[C.C.]
The Japan Liberation Front:
the largest insurgent
group in Area 11.
Viceroy Cornelia was
determined to crush them.
She encircled the
Narita mountains where
her proud Britannian legions
applied overwhelming force,
sure their "inferior enemy"
was vanquished.
Then, the Black Knights
made their move.
Using the Guren Mk-II's
radiant wave surger,
they caused the water veins of
the summit to explode at once.
The mountain collapsed.
Both the Japan Liberation
Front and the main
Britannian forces were engulfed
in mud and rushing water.
Cornelia was isolated;
most of her forces lost.
Seeking an unprecedented
reversal, Zero commanded
the Black Knights to
hunt down Cornelia.
[C.C.] In their hearts, everyone
has faith in their own existence
and ultimate triumph.
However, when time
and destiny unfold,
this faith turns out to be
quite fleeting and pointless.
[DARLTON]
What are our losses?!
[SOLDIER 1] I've only got signal
from 20 percent of our forces.
[DARLTON]
20 percent?!
Our command structure
can't sustain this!
[FEMALE SOLDIER]
This is the Marceau unit!
I can't raise General Alex!
It looks like the second
division's been wiped out!
Lloyd, what's going on?
[LLOYD]
Hmm... It's very unnatural.
Unnatural?
There seems to be
an unconfirmed report
that the Black Knights
have appeared.
--Zero!
--[LLOYD] Congratulations!
This is our chance.
Lloyd!
You're so rash.
[LLOYD]
Huh? Why's that?
Would you like a
detailed explanation?
Uh, no, I'll pass.
Anyway, while the High Command's
still gathering data,
all we can do is
play it by ear, right?
[STAFF OFFICER A]
Is the Viceroy safe?
[STAFF OFFICER B] Yes,
she was outside the mud flow.
But the units guarding
her flank are lost.
That means she's
totally isolated.
What the hell are
those Purebloods doing?!
[KEWELL gasps]
Come on, move!
I can't lose to Elevens!
I am a Brittanian!
Lord Kewell!
[LELOUCH]
All right!
Guren MK-II, move to
the planned point!
We'll break through the last
of their line and take Cornelia!
--[KALLEN] Right!
--[OHGI] Got it!
[SUGIYAMA]
Let's pull this off!
[VILLETTA]
Fight to the death!
[SUGIYAMA yells]
[TAMAKI]
Sugiyama! You okay?!
[SUGIYAMA]
Y-Yeah...
[grunts]
[BOTH scream]
[squeals]
[BLACK KNIGHT 1]
Get them!
[LELOUCH]
That's right, move swiftly.
If you survive this battle,
you can call yourself
a true warrior.
And afterward...
[STAFF OFFICER A] The Purebloods
are holding their ground?
[SOLDIER 2] Yes, sir!
Under Lady Viletta's command!
[STAFF OFFICER B]
Then use the moment
for the Viceroy to retreat!
Send air cover!
No, wait!
Something's approaching
the Viceroy from behind!
[TOHDOH]
All units, are you ready?
[HOLY SWORDS]
Yes, sir!
[TOHDOH] All right.
Deploy the custom Burais.
[HOLY SWORDS]
Deploying!
[TOHDOH]
Listen carefully!
If this landslide was manmade,
it should allow us to hit
Cornelia from behind.
Capture Cornelia now!
Take revenge for what
happened seven years ago!
[HOLY SWORDS]
Yes, sir!
By the honor of
the Four Holy Swords!
[CORNELIA]
What?!
[GUILFORD]
Protect Her Highness!
[TOHDOH]
Surround them!
The Japan Liberation Front?!
[TOHDOH]
Slash and encircle!
[HOLY SWORDS]
Right!
These are not just any Burais.
This reminds me
of seven years ago.
But it's different now.
This time we have
Knightmares as well!
Your Highness, leave them to us!
Please, you have
to withdraw for now!
[CORNELIA] Very well, I know
a way to turn this around.
Guilford!
[GUILFORD]
Yes!
After you've driven them back,
meet me over at point nine!
Nine?
I understand!
[SENBA, URABE]
Cornelia!
[CORNELIA]
You weaklings!
[CORNELIA] All right!
Keep this up and crush Zero!
[TAMAKI] Maybe we should
get Kallen over here.
[LELOUCH]
No!
If we break formation now,
our plan is ruined!
[LELOUCH]
This is turning grim.
If it goes on, we'll be
fighting her royal guard next.
[INOUE] Zero! Cornelia's
under attack down below!
What's that?
Which team made the move?
[INOUE] It's not our people!
Looks like the JLF!
[LELOUCH] Someone else
understands my intent?
How excellent.
They'll hold off
the royal guard,
which is just what we need.
I'm sorry for the
late arrival, General!
Tohdoh! We've been waiting!
[TOHDOH] General, please
send all remaining units
to join me here.
[KATASE]
Can you beat them?
[TOHDOH] Yes, but only if we
can hold off their main force!
We have a chance now to
turn the entire war around!
[GUILFORD] I've heard Area 11
has a formidable commander.
Their "shining knight."
Is this him? Tohdoh?!
Fine! Let him try me!
Urgh! At a time like this?!
[SOLDIER 3]
What do we do?
[DARLTON]
Fall back!
We have to find a way to link up
with Viceroy Cornelia.
[SOLDIER 3] But sir, their main
base is right in front of us!
And if we're hit from behind,
we'll be wiped out!
You fool!
If Princess Cornelia's
taken by these Elevens,
this entire battle is lost!
[SOLDIER 3]
Y-Yes sir! [screams]
[STAFF OFFICER A] Sub-Viceroy
Euphemia,
you must act now
to prevent a disaster.
Send in the G1!
[EUPHEMIA]
No!
[STAFF OFFICER B] But Commander
Guilford is completely
pinned down;
he can't get to Cornelia.
Her life is at stake here!
We can't!
There's a field hospital
right here! And civilians!
They've been evacuated
from all over the area
and brought to this point!
Besides, the G1 base
is our command center!
The Viceroy ordered me not
to move it, no matter what!
That's why...
I just can't...!
[gasps]
Well, hello there, the ASEEC's
crew reporting for duty.
[STAFF OFFICER A]
Insolence!
[STAFF OFFICER B]
You're irregulars!
Your orders are to
keep silent and observe!
Um, yes sir,
normally we would, but...
But all of this waiting
around is boring.
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Sub-Viceroy Euphemia...
I beseech you, please
order us into the battle!
[STAFF OFFICER B]
How transparent!
You just want the glory
of rescuing the Viceroy!
[STAFF OFFICER A]
Our whole army is out there!
You think one unit is
going to change things?!
With an Eleven pilot!
[LLOYD] Right, right, but
what's the harm in trying?
Since it's just one unit,
it won't look bad for you
if we lose, right?
[gasps]
[LLOYD]
Are you listening?
[EUPHEMIA]
Euphie!
Yes, I understand.
Please do it!
We got it!
Thank you very much!
Right! I won't fail!
Dammit! He's fierce!
[TOHDOH]
Scatter!
[URABE] Lt. Colonel!
What about Cornelia?
If Zero's the man I think he is,
he's moving into
position right now!
We've got to trust him.
[GUILFORD]
What? Zero's on the move?!
[VILLETTA]
Right.
We'll keep going and
come over and back you up!
Never mind that now,
just track Zero!
[VILLETTA]
Y-Yes, sir!
This is his projected course.
[GUILFORD gasps] The Princess
was trying to trap Tohdoh;
now there's a Knightmare
waiting for her!
Princess Cornelia!
[CORNELIA]
I got the message, Guilford.
[CECILE] Advanced weapon
system Z-01 Lancelot,
utilize sand panels
to climb liquefied slope
at max combat speed
and rescue the Viceroy!
[SUZAKU]
Yes, my lord.
[LLOYD] Suzaku, there's
one thing I want to ask you.
[SUZAKU]
What's that?
[LLOYD] More than anything,
you hate when people die,
yet, you're in the military.
Why is that?
I'm in the military to stop
people from dying.
And that self-contradiction
will get you killed someday!
Ugh! Sorry about that!
Lancelot, now launching.
Cornelia!
[CORNELIA]
Lowborn scum!
[KALLEN gasps]
What's this?!
That's not just
a customized unit!
[receiver beeps]
Can you hear me, Cornelia?
This is checkmate.
[CORNELIA]
Zero!
[LELOUCH] Yes. Should we
celebrate our reunion?
Of course, you'll have
to surrender to us first.
And after that, there are a few
questions I wanna ask you.
And in case you're wondering,
your reinforcements
won't get here in time.
I win, Cornelia.
[CORNELIA]
You're a fool, Zero!
This one!
If I take this one out,
I'm free and clear!
You've got some moves!
[KALLEN growls]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[CORNELIA]
Coward! Attacking from behind!
Really?
And your own attack methods
don't show acts of cowardice?
[DARLTON] They launched a pincer
assault before we could regroup!
I'll never be able to
reach the Princess now!
[screams]
[SENBA]
Lt. Colonel,
we've crushed the
enemy reinforcements!
[TOHDOH]
Right!
Switch to spinning
life-or-death formation!
[HOLY SWORDS]
Yes, sir!
[GUILFORD] If this goes on,
Princess Cornelia will be....
[CORNELIA]
Guilford...
Guilford, my knight.
You and Darlton protect Euphie.
[GUILFORD]
Your Highness!
[CORNELIA]
I won't surrender.
As an imperial princess,
I'll fight to the last!
[GUILFORD gasps]
[GUILFORD]
Princess Cornelia!
Huh. She's so predictable.
[gasps]
Oh my.
As reckless as ever, eh?
He's used the V.A.R.I.S.
to clear the obstacles
in his path.
[SUZAKU]
Viceroy, are you all right?
I came to help, Your Highness!
[CORNELIA] Special Corps?
Who authorized you?
He can get her out of there
if it's the Lancelot unit.
[TAMAKI]
Hey, isn't that Knightmare--
[OHGI] Yeah. The one from
Shinjuku and Lake Kawaguchi.
Again?! It's him again?!
MK-II, destroy that
unit immediately!
It's interfered with us enough!
Right!
[gasps]
You handle that thing!
I'll take out Zero!
Now you'll pay for Shinjuku!
[gasps] It's as fast
as the Lancelot?!
If I can take it down...
Is that all you've got?!
[growls]
Blocked!
[screams]
Hey! Are you okay?!
[KALLEN]
I am...
--[LELOUCH] Ohgi!
--Yes.
[LELOUCH]
How's the Guren MK-II?!
[OHGI] The right hand's wrecked.
We've gotta fix it.
[growls] Retreat!
All Black Knights,
move to your escape points!
This has become a war
of attrition. Retreat!
[SUZAKU]
Viceroy!
Go after Zero!
[SUZAKU]
But--
My energy filler's just drained!
Go!
[SUZAKU]
Right!
[TAMAKI] Ugh, I'm hating
this retreat thing.
[OHGI] We thrashed 'em,
but if we keep pushing...
Face it, we left the JLF there
as bait while we ran away.
I hate when you say it
like that, but...
Yeah, but people aren't
just pieces in a chess game.
Zero wouldn't think like that.
If he did, he'd end up
using us as pawns, too.
I don't believe he'd do that.
His rage is real.
He hates Britannia
as much as we do.
And I think a person who
knows rage also knows sorrow.
[LELOUCH growls]
Special corps head trailer.
Found Zero.
Going in for capture.
[SUZAKU]
Zero, I owe you; I know that.
You've saved a lot of people.
I know there are lots of Elevens
supporting you from the shadows.
However, your methods are...
...very wrong.
[growling]
[gasps]
[SUZAKU gasps]
Th-That's...
Is it the girl from the
capsule in Shinjuku?!
Stop now!
Don't even think
about hurting him!
[ZERO]
C.C...
She's working with Zero?
[ZERO]
Wait! What are you doing?
You're challenging
a Knightmare?!
It's a problem if you die.
It'll be indirect contact,
but it's worth a try.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Father... You're dead!
That's impossible!
No! I didn't mean to!
No, I... I just...!
[ZERO] Hey! Are you
using Geass on him?
[C.C.] I'm just feeding him
some shock images.
I can't tell what
he's seeing though.
Anyway, you've got time
to get away now.
[ZERO]
What about you?
[C.C.]
I can't move yet.
You go first!
[ZERO]
Don't be foolish.
I can't keep owing you favors--
[LELOUCH gasps]
[gasps] No, not now!
[grunts]
[LELOUCH whimpers]
[CITY PEOPLE yelling]
[LELOUCH]
What? This is different.
That's...
[C.C.]
S-Stop it!
Stay... out... of my mind!
[CITY PEOPLE screaming]
Stop it!
Why now?!
[C.C.]
You're... unveiling me...
[SUZAKU yells]
I had to do it!
[LELOUCH gasps]
[CITY PEOPLE
moaning, screaming]
[roaring, screaming]
[SUZAKU screams]
[gasps]
[ZERO gasps]
[ZERO]
What's happening to him?!
[C.C.]
Idiot! Get away now!
[gasps]
[ZERO]
C.C.!
[C.C. grunts]
Hurry! [screams]
[CHIBA]
Damn you!
[TOHDOH]
Don't follow!
I have no idea what
Zero is trying to do now.
Our only course of action
is to get to the General
and get him out of here.
Your Highness!
I'll be right there!
[CORNELIA] Guilford, relay
this message to all units:
Prepare to retreat.
[gasps]
[CORNELIA] There's no reason
to waste the lives
of any more of my men.
Stay in formation and
fall back cautiouslly.
We have to face facts.
We've been defeated this time.
[BLACK KNIGHTS cheering]
You see? Britannia
sure had its hands full
just dealing with the
Liberation Front!
Yeah.
That gave us the chance
we needed to escape.
[KALLEN]
Hey, where's Zero?
I can't raise his Burai.
You don't think he's been
captured, do you...?
[LELOUCH] This girl,
she can't be human.
She recovers from wounds in
ways that are beyond normal.
She was shot in the head
in Shinjuku, and yet...
Clovis confined her for
his private experiments,
so she's not connected
with Britannia.
Her vital signs are
at human levels.
I'd better analyze
a blood sample later
and photograph the wounds.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[LELOUCH]
What?
[gasps]
You finally called me...
by my real name.
[CORNELIA]
So Zero escaped again.
[GUILFORD] The Japan Liberation
Front hammered our defenses
and he slipped away
in the confusion.
Despicable. Using someone
else to cover his movements.
Oh, what about Kururugi?
[GUILFORD]
He's safe now.
We had to wait till his
energy filler ran out
to finally stop him.
[CORNELIA]
Stop him from what?
Was there a problem
with his unit?
[GUILFORD] Apparently.
It was going berserk.
[CORNELIA] A failure unworthy
of my older brother's forces.
[LELOUCH] I removed the shrapnel
and cleaned the wound.
[C.C.]
That wasn't necessary.
[LELOUCH]
Apparently not.
[C.C.] So, there was no point
in protecting me at all.
Your pride always
gets in the way
at the most ridiculous moments.
But then I learned
something from it.
Hmph.
[water drop echoes]
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
That's your name, isn't it?
You have a bad habit
of eavesdropping.
[LELOUCH]
Well, it's a good name.
It's a lot more
human than C.C...
[C.C.]
Oh, that's a joke.
As if I want to be more human.
After all,  I've-- I...
[C.C.]
I've forgotten everything.
Every single thing...
So what's the use of it?
A name? But why?
It's a good time
to say this. Yes...
You saved me today.
[LELOUCH]
You did that before
and gave me Geass. That's why
I'll only say this once...
[LELOUCH]
Thank you.
No one's ever...
thanked me before.
Well then, can you
show your appreciation?
Say it again,
like you did before.
[LELOUCH]
Uh? Oh, you mean the name.
[C.C.] Just this once,
with tenderness,
like you treasure
it in your heart.
Very well then...
[inaudible]
[LELOUCH]
How was that?
[C.C.] It was bad.
It was completely bad.
It wasn't tender. There was
no honesty or sympathy in it.
You spoke it oddly.
And worst of all, it was cold.
You're a picky girl.
Exactly. That's why
I go by the name C.C.
Ugh. Another soldier.
[RESEARCHER A] No wonder
our battalions fell apart!
[horn honking]
I swear I'm not Orange.
ZERO!
[KALLEN grunts]
[ZERO]
Looks like our ride's here.
[KALLEN]
Zero! Are you okay?
The others went on
ahead, and--
Who's that?!
[ZERO]
Oh, you needn't worry.
She's a very important friend.
[C.C. gasps]
[KALLEN]
Huh...?
[ZERO] C.C., I don't know
why snow is white,
but I still think
snow is beautiful.
I don't hate it.
I see.
[growls]
[LELOUCH]
Still not enough!
I need something more
to checkmate Cornelia.
And I have a feeling that
what's missing is inside of me.
Something I have
to face and overcome.
Then, I can lead the
Black Knights to the next stage.
Yes.
And if necessary, I'll even...