Ohgi, are you sure you wanna
go through with this?
[OHGI]
Yeah.
I have a duty to get
everyone to safety.
[MINAMI]
But...!
[OHGI]
No.
I'm just sorry
I did this to you.
Everyone...
In a battlefield
controlled by F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
Another F.L.E.I.J.A. strike...
Twammi fleet is
totally obliterated!
The operation--
I'm not going to stop it!
Stay just out of
the Damocles' range!
The Avalon falls
back as ordered!
All units! Attack in waves
and force the Damocles
to continue launching
F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
[NUNNALLY]
How easily... It's so easy...
...for me to--
[SCHNEIZEL] Nunnally, we're
ready to fire the next one.
[sobs] Right.
It renders tactics useless.
[JEREMIAH] However... If I
can get within a tight range,
they won't be able to use it!
A blaze luminous!
But it's so immense!
The Damocles was specially
designed and built
to achieve absolute
air superiority.
[CECILE] If it reaches
a certain altitude,
we'll lose our only
chance against it!
[LELOUCH]
Tch! Suzaku!
Can you break through
those defenses?!
[SUZAKU]
I'm trying!
But their power output is in
a different league than mine!
But I don't think they can
fire a F.L.E.I.J.A. now.
[C.C.]
And, in turn, our attacks can't
break through their shield.
We may as well be spectators.
Is there nothing
left for the world
except to cower before
the crushing might
of the F.L.E.I.J.A.s?
[LLOYD] Well, that offers
a sort of peace, too.
Mass our remaining
forces around the Avalon!
We're going to launch a direct
assault on the Damocles
with our hostages on board!
Sure about that?
[LELOUCH]
Your return here means
it's nearly figured
out, I presume.
The rest depends
on you and Suzaku,
Your Majesty.
Schneizel!
Are you trying to kill
the captives, too?!
[SCHNEIZEL] Now that the Black
Knights have been beaten--
[XING-KE]
We aren't beaten yet!
[SCHNEIZEL] Very well then,
I'll wait ten minutes.
Ten minutes?!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Aren't you talking to me because
you're already in
position to counterattack?
All right, fine. Ten minutes.
[KANON] That's a hefty loan,
sir, considering we need
ten minutes to
prep the next shot.
[SCHNEIZEL] It saves me
from dealing with them
after the battle.
[DIETHARD]
Are you saying you don't need
the Black Knights anymore?
What purpose would a collective
military strength
possibly serve?
[MILLY]
Hey, Rivalz.
[RIVALZ]
What's up, Prez?
It's amazing. I mean,
when you think about it,
our student council
members are out
fighting the whole world.
What, is that sarcasm?
'Cause I wasn't able to
protect Nina, correct?
Don't beat yourself up.
You did your very best.
I tried, but I...
No. You really did.
From behind?!
[yelps]
[HOSTAGES gasp]
[SUZAKU]
The Black Knights!
I'll defeat you myself, I swear!
[LELOUCH]
Sneaking from behind, Xing-ke?
[SUZAKU] I won't let
the Avalon be shot down!
Xing-ke, you'll fail!
Justice weighs on my side!
[grunts, coughs]
[SUZAKU]
It's over!
What the--?!
[TOHDOH]
Kururugi!
[SUZAKU] You dare fight
in your condition?!
You turned your
back on your country
in order to climb in rank, so
here is the ugly way it ends!
What is this you fight for?!
The one thing I want that
I'll fight for is a future!
[TOHDOH]
Your future is worthless!
I failed!
[CHIBA]
General!
[SUZAKU yells]
Dammit!
Oh?
They've done better
than I expected.
[OPERATOR]
Primary float, damaged.
Damage level, 75%.
It's failed. The
Avalon is falling!
[SUZAKU]
I can't let them board it!
[TAMAKI]
Hold it, hold it, hold it!
Okay!
Now to settle things
once and for a--
Huh? I'm not giving in!
I've got pride, too, ya know!
I wasn't in time.
Did they get in?
[XING-KE] If we engage
them in close combat,
we've a chance
to take over their
power and communications,
then rescue the hostages!
We hear and obey!
Holding out this long
was good enough.
Land the ship in the Pacific.
You will now follow
mission Apate Aletheia.
[SAYOKO]
Master Lelouch...
[LELOUCH]
You have served me well.
I'm grateful for the
resolve you've all shown.
[SAYOKO, LLOYD, CECILE]
Yes, Your Majesty.
[meows]
[SCHNEIZEL] Should we fire
another F.L.E.I.J.A. now?
[KANON]
We still have our blaze luminous
and should wait for criticality.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Good point.
But it's an excellent
opportunity to eliminate
the Black Knights.
No, I suppose we shouldn't.
That's too ambitious.
[LELOUCH]
Yes, I understand.
This is a personal request
from me. However...
[NINA] It was Princess
Euphemia's wish, too, wasn't it?
Yes, which is why
I have to do it.
But for the device
to be complete,
the environmental data
needs to be entered into
the final program.
You should let me go with you--
No, you've done
enough for me, Nina.
What you just said reveals
your true feelings about this.
Yes, you've done enough for me.
For Zero, Euphy's murderer.
I won't find it in my
heart to forgive Zero.
Maybe not for the
rest of my life. But...
This is separate from that.
I simply had to
find my own answer
to everything that's happened.
That's all there is to it.
[LELOUCH]
You're truly amazing.
C.C.! Are you all right?
[C.C.]
Well, that's a switch.
Were you really
worried about me?
You're a valued combatant.
[C.C.] Hmph. That's why
I came to pick that up.
Then... will you
be escorting me?
You're going out there?
Though taking such
action could mean you'll
have to kill Nunnally yourself.
I have no choice if
she stands in the way
of the Zero Requiem.
Lelouch, don't you
hate me for cheating you
out of your own life?
By giving you your Geass,
I affected your life and
drastically changed your fate.
That doesn't sound like you,
the immortal witch.
C.C... the Geass
power you gave me...
It only put me on the
path that would lead
to my destiny, and nothing more.
Everything that followed
was my choice.
[C.C.] In all my life,
I've never met a man like you.
[LELOUCH]
C.C...
[rumbling]
Kallen!
[KALLEN]
I'm going to stop you!
Goodbye, Lelouch.
[KALLEN grunts]
[C.C.] Leave this to me!
Get to the Damocles!
You stubborn--!
Stop! You're no
match for the Guren!
[C.C.] I'm sincerely glad
that you care, Lelouch.
[gasps]
[C.C.]
Now go on, hurry!
Just make sure you come back!
That'll make me smile, okay?
Yes! I promise you!
I have to succeed,
no matter what!
This move must work!
[OPERATOR]
Enemy Knightmares approaching.
The Shinkirou is leading them.
Lower the blaze luminous
away from the F.L.E.I.J.A.
launch tube, immediately.
We're going to redirect
our aim at the Shinkirou.
Lelouch, discarding
your life at the end?
How unsightly.
[OPERATOR]
Realignment complete.
Nunnally. It ends now.
Can you do this?
[NUNNALLY]
Yes,
brother Schneizel.
[OPERATOR]
Blaze luminous, lowered.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Now.
[NUNNALLY whimpers]
Right. Entering data.
[NINA] The F.L.E.I.J.A.
changes composition
from moment to moment.
If we collide it with
a reaction corresponding
to that composition,
we can prevent it
from reaching criticality.
[LLOYD]
However, you need to input
the local environment data
just prior to detonation,
within a 19 second time frame.
[CECILE] And, even if you
complete the program,
you'll only have 0.04
seconds to execute.
With this, peace will come.
Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
Yes, Your Majesty!
[growls]
[SUZAKU]
Now!
[NINA]
It should work in theory, but...
Princess Euphemia...!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hm?
A F.L.E.I.J.A.!
It disappeared!
It worked? They did it?
In 19 seconds and then
in 0.04 seconds?
[SCHNEIZEL] I didn't
expect them to have made
a toy like that.
Ready... Fly in!
They gotten through the blaze?!
They have indeed.
[NUNNALLY gasping]
[OPERATOR]
Enemy infiltration, alpha-three!
Where's the key?! I must
find the Damocles key!
[OPERATOR]
Delta block communications cut!
Float control room six
has been destroyed!
Prince Schneizel!
My kudos, Lelouch. I salute you.
For forcing me to
implement my final plan.
Huh?! You're really
going to do that?!
--[DIETHARD] Hm?
--[SCHNEIZEL] Yes.
Turn the Damocles into a prison
for Lelouch and the others.
[SCHNEIZEL]
After we've abandoned ship,
we'll obliterate the Damocles
entirely with a F.L.E.I.J.A.
What a fine coffin for him.
I'm certain you'll be
pleased with it, Lelouch.
[SUZAKU] If Damocles
reaches satellite orbit,
even the Lancelot will
be useless against it.
To win, we need
to stop Schneizel.
[LELOUCH] I'm analyzing
the internal structure.
I have to break the password.
What?!
Gino?
[GINO] Lelouch! I refuse to
accept you and your Britannia!
I'll destroy you, here and now!
[LELOUCH]
Guh?! How is it so powerful?!
[SUZAKU]
Gino!
Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch, go on ahead!
There's an enemy to be defeated
and someone to be rescued!
It's all up to you now! Go!
[LELOUCH]
Right!
[GINO]
Coward!
[LELOUCH grunts]
[SUZAKU]
You insist on fighting me, Gino?
Yes.
I will do whatever it takes
to protect something I love!
And I'm fighting for
the same reason!
[GINO]
To protect what?!
[LELOUCH] Is Schneizel on the
control and command floor?
Or else, could he be...?
[OPERATOR]
Seventh sequence.
F.L.E.I.J.A. detonation point
set to within Damocles!
Damocles and the F.L.E.I.J.A.s
are simply machines in the end.
We can always rebuild them.
But, sir, you know
the Toromo Agency
doesn't have the resources.
Nor does Rosenberg.
Yes...
But Lelouch is now
the enemy of the world.
If it turns out that our system
has destroyed him... There will
be plenty of organizations
happy to build
F.L.E.I.J.A.s for us.
Isn't that basically terrorism?
Besides, there's
Princess Nunnally's opinion
to consider, also.
Why care for what she says?
Bait has no opinion.
What do you mean--
you're abandoning her?!
World peace or a single life?
It's sad to say, but one cannot
be compared with the other.
[NUNNALLY grunting]
Where is it? Where's the key?
I have to stop Lelouch!
[JEREMIAH]
We have to hold out here until
His Majesty completes
his mission!
I despise what Lelouch is now.
[JEREMIAH]
The Knight of Six?!
Now that's a fitting
opponent for me!
[KALLEN] You have no country!
You have nothing to avenge!
You also don't have
a shred of ambition!
Someone who has
no reason to fight
should just leave!
[C.C.] I've made a reason
to fight! A promise!
[KALLEN] Are you saying
that you love Lelouch?!
[gasps]
[C.C.]
I don't know.
But I believe the time
has finally arrived
for me to stop "accumulating
experiences" and start living.
[KALLEN] That makes you
sound almost human!
Well done.
Kallen, I concede. You win.
Don't care, 'cause to
me, it doesn't matter.
Bye now.
Heh.
Winning or losing,
I never would have thought
that those feelings were still
inside me, alive and well.
[NUNNALLY]
The key... Where's the key?!
It's got to be here!
I have to stop Lelouch, and
it's all up to me to do it!
If only I could--
[NUNNALLY gasps]
[SOLDIER A]
Standing by to launch.
Rendezvous point with
Sir Hartgren is as planned,
no changes.
Course clear. Ceiling favorable.
--[beeping]
--[SCHNEIZEL] Huh?
[grunts]
I've been waiting
for you, Schneizel.
I see.
I suppose this means that
you have me in checkmate.
[grunts]
Please tell me.
I'm dying to know.
Just how did you discover
what my plan was?
You're mistaken.
What I anticipated was the
pattern of your own nature.
My nature?
[LELOUCH] You don't have
the desire to win.
[SCHNEIZEL grunts]
You remember that chess match?
At the Vermillion
Forbidden City?
And the coup d'etat
of the Black Knights...
You only play games
you can't lose.
So...
...you predicted that I
would abandon the Damocles?
Schneizel, this time,
I'm going to make sure
that you lose.
Meaning I'll be put to death.
Hong-Gu, move from corridor
three to take the bridge.
--U.F.N. representatives--
--[elevator doors opening]
[gasps] Xing-ke...!
Your Majesty! You're all right?
Yes! We were saved by
those people over there!
That's correct.
Master Xing-ke, we are
now on your side.
You all betrayed Lelouch then?
Huh?
And for a valid reason.
He threatened us!
However, now that Lelouch
is no longer here...
[KAGUYA] At the very least,
we believe that the others
think dictatorship is wrong
and will never support it.
Very well then.
[VILLETTA] Yes. The final
battle will most likely
take place within the Damocles.
Ohgi--I mean the
Secretary General--
Either way.
You're saying he's okay, right?
Y-Yes...
[CORNELIA]
My brother didn't kill me.
I'm still here after
all is said and done.
In a more normal world,
he'd be an excellent ruler.
He isn't driven by the
ambition that egotists have.
I was a fool not
to have seen that.
Wouldn't you agree?
[gasps]
Princess, I...
[sobs]
Guilford.
You're never going to stop
calling me that, are you?
[GUILFORD sobs]
I have a question.
We're you intending to
use the Damocles as a tool
to dominate the world?
I wasn't.
I only wanted to give
everyone what they wanted.
To bring peace to civilization.
[LELOUCH] Disregarding
humanity's true nature?
That's a matter of opinion.
Then you actually imagined
you could maintain
the world in a
perpetual state of "now."
But...
...life without change might be
called anything except life.
It's nothing more
than experience.
But...
...link those together, and
they become knowledge, right?
Schneizel, you truly
are superior.
So superior, you
can't even see it!
Yes. Emperor Charles
sought the past.
You seek the present.
But I seek the future.
[SCHNEIZEL]
But the future may be prove
to be worse than the present.
[LELOUCH]
No... It will be better.
Because, no matter
how long it takes,
people will continue
to seek out happiness.
Even though that will end up
making people greedy.
[laughs]
Your folly also knows no limit.
You're really too
emotional about this.
Hope and dreams are merely
names for aimless fiction.
You're restricted,
since you belong
to the symbol known
as a royal family,
which looks down on the world.
I've seen it over and over.
The people who
struggle against sadness.
Those who seek the future.
How they all carry on,
wishing for happiness.
Human nature is
why I chose Geass
and to wear a mask.
Lelouch, you're
contradicting yourself.
You, who continually
deny the will of others,
are standing here before us,
affirming the will of humanity.
That's enough. Kill me
now and be done with it.
But... a F.L.E.I.J.A.
will still decimate you.
We will gladly give
our lives to bring peace
to the world--
Hm?
And that's how I
came to my decision...
...that I'd give you
the gift of the words.
"You shall serve Zero."
Then you never intended
to kill me at all.
You wanted to...!
H-Highness!
Dammit! Why didn't
I see it coming?
He anticipated
Schneizel's thoughts
and recorded that
conversation...!
Order me to do whatever
you wish, Master Zero.
[DIETHARD grunts]
[SCHNEIZEL]
Schneizel... your willingness
to let yourself be killed
is exactly what has
led you to be defeated.
[DIETHARD grunts]
Don't move!
[GUARD 2 gasps]
Zero! This story's finished!
You never should
have come this far!
You shouldn't even
be alive, you bastard!
[gun fires]
[DIETHARD groans]
What right have you
to deny my existence?
You have none.
[thud]
[KANON]
Prince Schneizel...
A man would sacrifice his own
life without any hesitation...!
Such is the power of Geass!
Z-Zero... At least...
...finish me with
your Geass, too.
Sorry, Diethard,
you're just not worth
wasting my Geass on.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] Now, Schneizel,
you can begin by canceling
the self-destruct
for the Damocles.
[SCHNEIZEL] Understood.
However, Nunnally is the one
who has the F.L.E.I.J.A.
control switch.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[SUZAKU]
It doesn't matter how strong
you made your machine!
You won't beat me!
We'll see about that!
[gasps]
And this is the result... Gino.
No, I've done what
I came to do here.
He damaged the
blaze luminous system?
[GINO]
Now, Kallen!
[KALLEN]
Thanks, Gino!
Suzaku! I've come to end it!
Our continually crossing paths!
[SUZAKU gasps]
[NUNNALLY]
It's you, isn't it, big brother?
It is.
The reason you're
here must be this.
Did you come for
the Damocles key?
[LELOUCH] Yes. It's dangerous.
Dangerous to you.
[NUNNALLY]
Then that's why.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
Why...
I won't close my eyes
to things any longer.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
She's broken father's Geass?!
With her own will?!
[NUNNALLY]
Now, Lelouch...
Will you use your Geass
on me, as well?
[LELOUCH]
Perhaps I've only been wandering
since that day we first met.
I was so sick of a world
that never changed.
But...
I couldn't give in
to the despair
by telling lies to myself.
Yes... My name...
My personal history...
The power I've gained...
Maybe... it's all
been a path for me,
at the end of which
I'll find the truth.
Perhaps that's what
I've sought all along.
Well, then...