[C.C.] For now,
there is still tomorrow.
For Lelouch Lamperouge, it is
a tomorrow he can dream of...
And that dream
is based on Geass,
the power given to him by
a mysterious girl named C.C.
It is the absolute power to
compel anyone to obey him.
Using his Geass,
Lelouch is determined to destroy
the Holy Britannian Empire.
...to avenge the death
of his mother...
...and to create a world where
his younger sister, Nunnally,
can live in peace.
Japan is now a colony
known only as Area 11.
Here, his vow is made
to change the world.
[ALL]
Huh?
[POLITICIAN]
A child?
[ROLO]
That's right,
I can't remember how
many people I've killed.
[gunshot]
[ROLO] Nobody counts the number
of times they brush their teeth
or eat a meal.
Same with this.
[ROLO] My Geass is
suited to assassination.
That's what I was told.
So I kill. There was
no other place for me.
An under-cover operation
I'll be playing someone's
little brother.
Are you sure this is the
right assignment for me?
I've never known any parents
or family, so it doesn't seem--
No. If that's the
order I'm given...
...then my big brother
shall be Lelouch Lamperouge.
[LELOUCH] Your Geass is
the power to stop time?
I have no reason to answer you.
The orders given to
me are as follows:
If Lelouch Lamperouge's
memories return...
...if Zero is awakened,
then he is to die.
[LELOUCH]
Sixteen...
Seventeen. Eighteen.
--Nineteen.
--What's that?
--Why are you counting?
Since the moment you appeared,
I've been counting the seconds
to myself, carefully,
one by one.
But now the count
is out of synch.
Now, why do you think that is?
I'll make you my pawn
to find Nunnally.
Rolo, you can't stop
time, no one can.
You've just altered
my sense of time.
Understanding that doesn't help
you; you still can't beat me.
[ROLO]
That's absolute.
No one can live in the
same time flow with me.
[LELOUCH]
You're correct, Rolo,
but that doesn't
help you either.
You'd like to kill me
now, but you can't,
and we both know the reason why.
If I die, you won't gain either
of the two things that you want.
Two things?
First, you won't get C.C.,
for whom I've been
the bait in your hunt.
But if you let me go,
I can draw her out for you.
I'll help you get her.
You'd sell out C.C. like that?
She isn't worth my own life;
survival comes first.
And what's the other thing?
[LELOUCH]
Your life.
[ROLO]
Ha.
Like I care about that.
[LELOUCH]
Rolo, what is the future?
The future is hope.
Without hope your life is
on hold. Empty. Waiting.
And you have no hope
beyond your mission, Rolo.
If you capture C.C., what sort
of future will it open for you?
Things will just go on as they
are and nothing will change.
But this is my mission.
[LELOUCH] Kill me and your
mission will never be completed.
You wanna capture
C.C., don't you?
Tomorrow, I'll lure C.C.
out and she'll be yours.
Once that's done, your
new future will begin.
Don't worry. I would
never lie to you.
[LELOUCH]
Not to you anyway.
[KALLEN]
This reminds me of Aomori.
[C.C.]
It isn't as bad as that was.
At least everyone here
is wearing their clothes.
Zero used his Geass on
the consul general, right?
So, why are they doing this now?
Who knows.
Still, if they
run us out of here,
then we and Lelouch will be--
Split up all over again.
--[door opens]
--[C.C.] Hm?
How unexpected. You came alone.
I thought the United States
of Japan had been recognized
by the Chinese Federation
consul general.
[XING-KE]
He's going to be disposed of.
[C.C., KALLEN gasp]
Or do the Black Knights
choose to take
the path of destruction
right here?
[KALLEN]
Hold it!
You can't just spring that--!
[C.C.]
I see. You can arrange it
so it appears the consul
general is killed fighting us.
[KALLEN]
C.C.
It seems Zero is pulling a
trigger he never meant to pull.
Will this be noble ambition
or base treachery?
[LELOUCH]
Convincing Rolo to wait
bought me a little bit of time.
As long as he thinks
he can get C.C.,
he won't report that I've
regained my memories.
Still, what's his motivation?
Doesn't seem to be a desire
for promotion in Britannia,
nor simple loyalty.
Is there some other line of
question I should be following?
That's a dangerous card,
but it has its merits.
I don't have any
time to hesitate...
...'cause tomorrow,
Tohdoh and the others
are scheduled for execution.
So what do I do? Rolo knows
about my Geass now.
Even if I managed
to kill him somehow,
the O.S.I. would know that
I've regained my memories.
iIf that happens,
Nunnally will be--
[LELOUCH] It seems I'll
have to keep playing student
until I can rescue Nunnally.
Fortunately,
Guilford's men and the
Office of Secret Intelligence
don't seem to share information.
That explains why they haven't
found the Knightmare I hid.
But that's all I have in my
favor. So what should I do?
How do I save the Black Knights
and neutralize Rolo
at the same time?
[O.S.I. MEMEBER]
Unacceptable!
Did this kid kill Bruno
in cold blood or not?
And he was the fifth one.
All Victor did was
touch the kid's locket,
and the next thing--
Victor had his own
personality problems.
You don't kill a man
because of that!
Now that there's this guy
claiming to be Zero,
we have to get our
priorities straight
and pull the team together.
That's exactly right,
and I'm not teaming up with
the freakin' Angel of Death!
[ROLO] Team? The mission is
what's important, isn't it?
Who cares about the team?
Hey, Ohgi, is this new Zero
the same as our Zero?
I wish I knew.
Either way, don't
get your hopes up.
He'll probably abandon us again.
[GUILFORD] What was the
source of the explosion
in the consulate?
[BART] They haven't
issued a formal statement.
[ALFRED] They've given their
approval for the executions,
that's all we've heard.
[GUILFORD]
Hmph.
These executions are a crude
show to frighten the Elevens.
What a vulgar approach this is.
You think Zero will dare
to show himself?
Even if he doesn't,
we still come out ahead.
If this "Zero" can't
pull off a miracle,
he'll never gain the
support of the people.
You've thought it through
that far, Lord Guilford?
[GUILFORD] In any case,
I want him to show up.
Or rather, I pray
deeply that he does.
For the sake of Her Highness,
wherever she is now.
[XING-KE] Why did you
recognize the U.S.J.?
On your own,
without confirmation from
the Vermillion Forbidden City?
Even if you are one
of the High Eunuchs,
that was unforgivable.
Just what were you
planning to use Zero for?
I'd no intention to
use Zero for anything!
Zero must be pleased
in every way!
And the Empress's
feelings on this?
That little wench
doesn't matter.
The absolute law is that Zero
shall bring happiness to me.
[XING-KE]
Simpering traitor!
The Crimson Dynasty is dead.
[LELOUCH]
It's no use!
Killing him, controlling
the data, disguising it.
No matter what plan I come up
with, Rolo remains an obstacle.
I need to confirm this data
before the execution starts.
[NEWSCASTER]
It looks like the execution
will be getting
underway shortly.
Once again, these are
the rebel terrorists
who formerly called themselves
the Black Knights.
Will Zero appear to stop the
execution of his followers?
[WOMAN 1]
Oh, Zero, please!
General Tohdoh...
Don't kill them.
Zero betrayed us when
we needed him most.
I doubt he'll show
up to save us.
He's gonna come. If he's
the real one, if he's alive,
then somehow, someway
he'll make a miracle happen!
A miracle? Ha.
[VILETTA]
Maintain tight surveillance.
It's a long shot,
but it's possible that
C.C. might show up.
[VILETTA]
Kaname Ohgi... this is the end.
[DAVID]
Show yourself, Zero.
My father, Andreas Darlton,
shall be avenged at last.
--[beeping]
--[DAVID] Hm?
I have top secret orders
from headquarters.
Communications are
being intercepted,
so I'm to deliver them
to you face-to-face.
[ROLO] Right, I'll be
borrowing your identity.
Tell me, how are we
supposed to interpret this?
If Zero appears, you're free
to do whatever you wish.
[C.C.] So, even if we start
shooting at the Britannians,
you can pretend that
you know nothing about it?
[XING-KE] That's not
such a bad deal, is it?
You may be a military officer,
but you can play
politics as well, I see.
[OFFICER]
Sir Kimmel,
any problems with the
A.S.E.E.C. mass-pro unit?
It may have some glitches left
from when the O.S.I.
was using it.
It's a high-value apparatus.
Report in if it
malfunctions in any way.
[KIMMEL]
This is Kimmel.
No problems with
Vincent. Moving out.
[ROLO] Lelouch, if you don't
keep your promise, you'll die.
[BART]
Lord Guilford.
[NEWSCASTER] It's almost
time for the execution.
The remaining members
of the Black Knights
shall feel the
judgement of justice.
Zero, please!
We're waiting for you!
To make a miracle!
[GUILFORD]
Elevens!
The Zero who you believed
in has not appeared!
It has all been a deception!
I challenged him to
a fair and honest duel,
and he has skulked
away like a coward.
Take aim!
Don't do it!
My friends.
[C.C.]
Don't move!
If you go out now,
you'll just die with them!
[KALLEN]
I know, but--
It's all right.
We fought well,
now let's die well.
[ZERO]
You're mistaken!
[gasps]
[ZERO]
You're wrong, Guilford!
He showed up! But still...
Hold back, we can't
jump into this.
If he's by himself,
what can he do?
[GUILFORD]
I see.
You snuck up behind me... Zero!
[ZERO] Guilford. Those aren't
terrorists you're executing!
They are the Black Knights!
Soldiers of the army of
the United States of Japan!
[GUILFORD]
You expect me to recognize them
as prisoners of war?
It's Zero!
So, you did come.
As expected.
But if you break your promise
to me, I'll kill you, Zero...
...or rather,
Lelouch Lamperouge!
[NEWSCASTER]
It's Zero. Zero has appeared.
What a reckless, foolhardy move.
[SAHINA]
Zero?
Yes, but why?
Is it the real Zero?
Of course it's really him! Zero!
[MAN] I remember they announced
their execution, but...
[MAN 2]
That's all that's been reported.
[MAN 3]
No... no!
[NEWSCASTER]
He's alone. Zero is all alone.
He is riding atop
a Knightmare Frame,
so apparently he's not
here to surrender.
However, if he intends
to fight alone...
See? He came just
like I said he would!
Then let's proceed
with the operational plan
that we started last year.
Assuming that Zero can wriggle
out of the little tight squeeze
he's gotten himself into.
[DIETHARD chuckles]
[DIETHARD] Sayoko, I would
like you to begin making
the arrangements
for our future.
[NEWSCASTER] ...commandos appear
to be waiting to see what...
Where's Lelouch?
He's with Rolo at the theatre.
They've been in there
for the last half hour.
[NEWSCASTER]
What will happen?
[ZERO] It's been quite
a while, Lord Guilford.
Why don't you come out,
and we can talk about
the good old days.
[GUILFORD]
Tempting as that invitation is,
I'll stay where I am.
We'll just settle
our past grudges
from the insides
of our Knightmares.
If Guilford won't come out,
Zero can't use his Geass.
[ZERO]
Hmph! How predictable of you!
Then let's set some rules!
[GUILFORD]
Rules?
[ZERO] The rules of our duel.
We'll settle this one-on-one.
Very well. No one else will
interfere with our combat.
[ZERO]
We will each have one weapon.
[GUILFORD]
Agreed!
I choose this as my weapon!
[ZERO] And for mine,
I shall borrow that shield.
[GUILFORD]
What? But, that's...
[ZERO]
It will do.
He's going into battle
with a riot shield?
So could it be
possible that he is...?
[TOHDOH]
Planning to kill himself?
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
[XING-KE]
You disappoint me, Zero.
[CHINESE ADJUTANT]
What shall we do?
[XING-KE] I owe him a debt
for giving me a perfect excuse
to get rid of that
parasite of a eunuch.
However, this is hardly a
pledge of endearing harmony.
If Zero turns out
to be incompetent,
then we'll just use the Black
Knights as our diplomatic tools.
I have a question
for you, Lord Guilford.
What do you do when
there is an evil
you cannot defeat by just means?
Do you stain your hands
with evil to destroy evil?
Or do you remain steadfastly
just and righteous
even if it means
surrendering to evil.
In either case, evil remains.
A paradox. Is it
merely word play?
In the name of Cornelia,
I choose justice!
I understand! In my case...
...I commit evil to
destroy the greater evil!
Yes, Your Highness.
What the--?!
[CROWD yelling]
[ASAHINA]
A-An Earthquake!
[TOHDOH]
No... This strategy is--
The same one from
the Black Rebellion!
Infantry unit 12!
Go to the control room on level
four! Zero's men are in there!
[gunshot]
Kallen, charge in
and take command!
[KALLEN] Right! Autonomous
armored knights, follow me!
Remember, rescuing Ohgi and
the others has top priority!
[BATTLE ALPHA 4]
Alpha 4 to Alpha 1! Respond!
Alpha 1! Somebody, answer me!
Disgraceful!
Yeah, one-on-one my ass!
Whoa!
[BART screaming]
No, Bart!
Black Knights, listen!
The enemy around me has
fallen into our territory!
Wipe out the Britannian forces
and save your comrades!
Our comrades...
He used the very structure of
the settlement against them?
[BLACK KNIGHT 1]
Hurry up!
Release everyone before the
Britannian forces can regroup!
They're going to escape.
Right into the
Chinese Federation.
C.C. is our primary
operational target.
Leave the military issues
to Lord Guilford.
These damned terrorists!
[KALLEN]
Britannia!
You're on notice: This is
Japanese territory now.
[ALFRED]
There is no Japan!
[KALLEN] Oh, really?
That's why I hate Britannians!
Goodbye, Eleven ace!
It's blocked at
this close range?!
[KALLEN]
This is the Radiant Wave Surger.
The moment you came in close,
my victory was assured.
So long.
[EDGAR]
Alfred! How dare you!
[CLAUDIO] Don't shoot! This is
Chinese Federation territory.
But--!
[CLAUDIO] There are
broadcast cameras all over!
[growls]
[SOLDIER]
Th-The Vincent!
The Vincent has charged inside!
I can't move from
here! Run for it!
[LELOUCH] You've come.
You've finally come... Rolo.
[ROLO]
So, you're running after all.
So much for your promise
to give me C.C.
Lelouch, you were lying
to me from the start.
[LELOUCH] Not yet!
I can't get caught yet!
[ROLO] All that talk
about giving me a future.
[LELOUCH]
I can't die here!
[ROLO] As long as I
complete my mission,
I'll open the way to my future!
[ROLO]
Oh, no.
I can't stop a physical object.
[ROLO]
It's gonna be a direct hit!
Am I gonna die in
a place like this?
[CLAUDIO]
David, stop!
If you hit the Chinese
Federation consulate,
it'll start a war with them!
[DAVID]
Understood.
But why?
Why did you save me?
Why would you?
[LELOUCH] Because you're
my little brother.
The memories may have
been planted in me,
but the time that you and
I spent together... was real.
[ROLO gasps]
[ROLO]
You're saying...
...all the things we did up
to now... they weren't lies?
[LELOUCH] Because you're
my little brother.
[ROLO]
Brother? Me?
That day... I'd never
had a birthday before,
and for the first time...
What about when you told me
your life... was more important?
Yet you risked
your life for this?
[LELOUCH]
I made a promise to you.
I promised you a new future.
Your future is with me.
[GUILFORD] Zero! Our grudges
will be settled now!
With one resounding blow...
...from this iron hammer!
[GUILFORD] What?! Sir Kimmel,
what's the meaning of this?!
Uh, no! I just--!
Don't tell me... you're
one of Zero's men?!
No!
[ROLO] I... If Lelouch dies,
then my mission is...
No, but... What am I doing?!
--[phone ringing]
--[ROLO gasps]
Uh, yes?
[LELOUCH] Rolo? Trouble.
It's Ms. Villetta.
I'll connect you
on a conference.
[VILETTA]
Rolo, where did you go?
I, uh...
Ms. Villetta, come on.
We can at least go to the
bathroom in peace, can't we?
So, what were you calling about?
[VILETTA] About the Chinese
consulate, of course.
[LELOUCH] Oh, yeah. Looks
like a real mess down there.
[ROLO]
Oh, no.
If they find out
what's happened,
I'll be thrown out
of the O.S.I.!
Even that person would...
[LELOUCH]
I understand.
I'll keep my little brother
out of danger like that.
[gasps]
Of course not.
A place where people
are being killed
is no place for a boy like Rolo.
Britannians, this is
your last warning!
Any further action will be
taken as armed intervention.
Withdraw at once!
[growls]
[TAMAKI]
Hey, hey!
[KALLEN]
Thank goodness! Ohgi!
Thanks, Kallen, from all of us.
[KALLEN]
Mh-hm.
And Tohdoh and the others.
Thank goodness!
Sorry for being so much trouble.
It must've been hard for you.
And for you as well.
Hey, who's in that
Knightmare over there?
I don't know.
It was an enemy unit, but I'm
not sure who's piloting it now.
Zero was protected.
Whoever it is,
it's not an adversary.
C.C.'s right there, but
now I can't take her in!
[LELOUCH]
From the beginning,
you never felt you
belonged with Britannia.
You belong... with me.
[LELOUCH]
Ha. He's mine now.
Only an amateur
leaves data like this
lying around a control room.
Apart from his Geass,
he's nothing to me.
Leaving me this guy's password
was very convenient.
And it worked like a charm.
Pattern Delta.
[LELOUCH]
Correct.
When Zero's unit takes
that course, aim carefully
and shoot the pursuing
Knightmare from behind.
After that, if Zero escapes,
destroy the opposing
Knightmare completely.
If he does not escape, go into
stand-by mode and await orders.
[DAVID]
Right. I've got it.
[LELOUCH laughing]
[LELOUCH]
Trying to take Nunnally's place,
you little little phony.
I'll use you up and then throw
you away like a piece of trash.
[LELOUCH] Who does Rolo
Lamperouge think he is?
Pretending he's really
is my little brother...
...I shudder from the disgrace.
It's too bad.
If you were someone who is
really loyal to the O.S.I.,
I could've had that sniper
finish you off right there.
Still, you'll make
a convenient pawn,
so I'll keep you in reserve
a little bit longer.
But never forget.
All you are is a fake Nunnally.
For now,
we'll play the game as if you
really are my little brother.
But one day I'll use you
for a most decisive move.