[C.C.] Lelouch, a young,
outcast prince of Britannia,
possesses two great powers:
One of them is the
absolute ability to compel
any person to do
whatever he commands.
The other is the Black Knights,
his military force assembled
with the intent of destroying
the Britannian Empire
ruled by his father.
Veiling his true identity behind
a mask and the code name Zero,
Lelouch has made his move
to avenge his mother's murder
and to create a world in which
his younger sister Nunnally
can find happiness.
What will be the final
outcome of these actions?
At this point,
no one can predict.
[VICE MINISTER]
The Japan Liberation Front
was nearly wiped out by your
Narita operation, Viceroy.
Now we're hunting down
the survivors one by one.
[CORNELIA]
Are you being sarcastic?
We're barely pulling our forces
back together after that fiasco.
[VICE MINISTER]
No! I-I didn't mean to--
[GUILFORD]
The occupation government
is responsible for this!
They've done nothing about
Area Eleven's subways
and mining railways!
In the ghettos, they falsify the
registries and property deeds,
as the rebellion
spreads unchallenged!
Uhh, the subway tunnels
stretch over the whole country.
We can't just fill them all in.
We don't have the budget.
[GUILFORD]
The terrorists are using them
as their strike bases
and escape routes!
[VICE MINISTER]
P-Prince Clovis instructed us--
[grunts]
Uh, he said...
...forcing them would
fuel the rebellion,
giving the Chinese Federation
an excuse to attack.
They've already
got their excuse!
Zero's growing stronger
and bolder every day!
[DARLTON] Vice-minister,
Internal Affairs has appointed
a special group of
Elevens to self-govern
this area, isn't that right?
A group who are
called the N.A.C.
[gasping]
When we stormed Narita,
we looked for evidence
of the N.A.C.'s conspiracies.
But it was buried
in the landslide...
Still our suspicions remain
high. If we supress them now...
[CORNELIA]
Hm...
A group of blue bloods
and plutocrats.
Relics of their dismal past.
[VICE MINISTER]
W-Wait, please!
These are just rumors; there's
no evidence of that at all!
I-If you suppress them,
then the Elevens' economy
will certainly collapse!
That means no tax revenue
to send to the homeland!
Also it's a prime directive
of the empire
that Numbers should take
care of their own kind!
And what have you done
to find the Black Knights?!
[VICE MINISTER] We unearthed
a shield machine they left
showing Zero was behind
the Narita operation.
B-But that's all we've got;
you can't squeeze information
out of corpses.
[CORNELIA]
So you can't catch Zero
and you don't want
us to hit Kyoto.
Do you know the word
"incompetent," minister?
It's for people who
can't get results.
[KIRIHARA]
So, the Britannian viceroy
has gone this far already.
[MUNAKATA] With the
Liberation Front smashed,
the last embers of Japan
have died away.
[OSAKABE]
No!
He may be on the run, but Toudou
is still strong, still fighting!
[KUBOIN]
Even if that's so,
I heard he lost his custom
Burais, so there's no hope--
[KAGUYA]
There IS hope.
[KIRIHARA]
Hm?
The Black Knights?
You've been enfatuated with Zero
since he rescued
Suzaku Kururugi.
We even sent him
the Guren MK-II.
[TEACHER] And after the defeat
at Trafalgar, Elizabeth the 3rd
found herself surrounded by
revolutionaries in Edinburgh.
--Oh, father...
--However, with the help
of Lord Britannia, she fled
to the American colonies,
now known as our
homeland, Britannia.
[SHIRLEY]
Hmm...
[SHIRLEY groans]
[groaning continues]
[SHIRLEY sighs]
Huh?
Okay, what's got you so worried?
Constipated? Your monthly?
[SHIRLEY]
Uh?! T-That's not it!
Ah. You're lonely 'cause
Lelouch is gone, aren't you?
We-eh...
It's more like, Kallen's
absent the same day he is.
Again...
Oh, so carefree while the
rest of the world grapples
with what happened at Narita.
Suzaku's been out for two days
because of that, too.
[SHIRLEY]
I know that!
But Lulu and Kallen?
Gone on the same day together?
That's serious!
[giggles]
[MILLY] I envy you, Shirley.
That's what I love about you!
[gasps]
[SHIRLEY]
Don't make fun of me!
[ARTHUR meows]
Then just tell him already!
Three little words:
"I like you!"
U-Uh... I couldn't!
I just couldn't!
I mean, what if--
[MILLY]
"What if he rejects me?!
It could ruin our
great friendship!"
[laughs]
You don't have to laugh
that hard, you know?
[MILLY]
It's comfortable, isn't it?
This place now.
The way we are together.
[SHIRLEY]
That's true.
[MILLY] Still, we should
prepare ourselves a bit.
The fact is, nothing stays
the same forever, you know.
[sighs]
Oh, forget it! Please don't
take me too seriously.
If it's bothering you,
why not just ask him
the next chance you get?
So, how do you feel
about it from your side?
[gasps]
[SHIRLEY] L-Lulu!
I thought you were absent!
Nunnally had a little
fever this morning.
And Sayoko was busy,
so I stayed home to help.
Oh, really? You don't say...
So is Nunna feeling better now?
[LELOUCH]
A bit.
Madame President, those papers?
Oh, right.
Make sure you organize all of
them by year and class, okay?
[LELOUCH]
Yeah, I will.
You have a talent for
ordering people around.
[MILLY]
And you're a great subordinate!
[LELOUCH] Subordinate?
I guess that's what I am.
Oh, Madame President!
You nearly gave me a
heart attack doing that!
Huh? Where's my tickets...?
Ah?!
Lulu!
[LELOUCH]
What is it?
[SHIRLEY] Um, is my dad's letter
mixed up with that paperwork?
[LELOUCH]
Hmm? Oh, sorry...
What's wrong?
Ah, Lulu!
Shirley?
Huh?
Stop being so suspicious.
That's hardly the case.
To me, he's nothing
more than a...
[SHIRLEY panting]
I did it!
I actually really did it!
So now what happens?
He'll come, right?!
I mean, he didn't say no.
Then again--uh-uh,
he's just coming with me
to little a concert...
So it's no big thing.
But, still, it's a chance!
[sighs]
Thank you, Father.
[phone rings]
[OHGI] Kyoto praised us for
using the Guren MK-II so well.
I thought that was encouraging.
[KALLEN]
But there was the White Armor--
[TAMAKI] Don't sweat it!
It was a tie, right? A tie!
[TAMAKI laughs]
[LELOUCH] Why would Shirley
just out of the blue...
My dad works a
long way from here,
but he likes to send me
great stuff like this
to keep my spirits up, y'know?
So, I was just wondering...
[OHGI]
Here.
[ZERO]
Hm? What's this?
[OHGI]
A love letter.
[ZERO]
Oh? From you?
[laughs] And they say
you have no sense of humor!
--[laughs]
--You laugh too much.
[OHGI] It's an official
letter from Kyoto.
They urgently request a meeting.
[ZERO] Is this really
such a big deal?
A big deal? It's Kyoto!
If they accept us,
it means funding and support.
It could solve
our financial crisis.
--[ZERO] Crisis?
--[OHGI gasps]
[ZERO]
There shouldn't be any problem
if you're following
the budget I laid out.
Well, uh...
Hey, it's not my fault!
We're turning into
a big organization now!
That means new
expenses, y'know.
Like fancy dinners for the new
recruits so you can show off?
Hey, you--
[KALLEN] I know where you've
been taking them, "big spender!"
You know about it?
[ZERO sighs]
[ZERO] We'll put Ohgi in charge
of the treasury for now.
Hold it right there! I'm the one
that's in charge of the cash!
That's my job!
[ZERO]
If you want me to trust you,
then show me some results.
Did you actually
just say "trust"?!
A guy who hides his face
from his own partners?!
How about it, Zero? Huh?!
Hold on, that's, uh...
[KALLEN]
Zero's not the problem here!
Who cares who he is?!
He had the skill to outwit
Cornelia, didn't he?
That's why he's the leader
of the Black Knights!
Do you really need
to know more?
[TAMAKI growls]
[NUNNALLY]
Nina is that you?
If you're not
feeling well, then...
[NINA]
Oh, no. It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
[TAMAKI sighs]
So what do we do?
I don't know...
[MINAMI]
We were in Naoto's unit.
[SUGIYAMA] I don't mind about
his kid-sister Kallen, but...
[TAMAKI] You were next
in line to be leader!
No one said that at Narita.
'Cause Zero
practically forced us.
[YOSHIDA]
We're the senior commanders,
and he keeps secrets from us!
[OHGI sighs]
[LELOUCH] I've narrowed it
down to 12 possibilites.
Now let's see
which bets pay off.
For that, I'll have to
meet them face to face.
--[knocking at door]
--[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Who is it?
[KALLEN]
It's me.
Um, I'm sorry if I was out of
line when I spoke up back there.
Kallen, tell me, do you wanna
know my identity as well?
[KALLEN grunts]
[KALLEN]
That girl knows, doesn't she?
No. Sorry to bother you.
[NUNNALLY]
Lelouch?
[LELOUCH]
Looks like your fever's gone.
Maybe I was just a little moody.
[LELOUCH]
Moody?
It just seems to me, lately,
that you've become
a little distant, like
you have other things
weighing on your mind.
[giggles]
Perhaps my body just did this on
its own to get your attention.
[LELOUCH]
You're wrong. I haven't changed.
No matter what, I'll always
be at your side, Nunnally.
So, then, can I be
a little selfish now?
Please hold my hand
just a little bit longer.
If I fall asleep alone...
I'm afraid, I'll have
that dream again.
[C.C.] You're serious?
You're asking me for a favor?
Yes. I got the idea from
something that you said.
No matter what Kyoto's
intentions are,
I want their power.
Is that what you
truly wish for?
If it's at the very core
of your reason for living,
then I'll try to help you.
Then do it.
C.C., I need you.
I understand. By the way,
you forgot something.
[LELOUCH grunts]
I didn't forget.
I don't know when
I'll be back tonight,
so I was planning to
call her and cancel.
Stick to your contract--
[phone rings]
It's me.
Oh, good timing.
I wanted to call.
--Y'see--
--[SHIRLEY] Um, listen, Lulu...
[LELOUCH]
Hmm?
[SHIRLEY] I-I know I made a date
with you, but I may be late.
Sorry, but, anyway I'm
sure it'll be fine, really!
But I promise you
that I'll be there.
Please bring your
command staff along,
as per my master's
instruction, understood?
[ZERO] They're patrolling the
perimeter in case
of any unpleasant contingencies.
I'll call them soon.
However, before I do...
[DISASTER BROADCASTER]
Severely damaged corpses
should be brought to tent 2.
I.D. all personal items.
Bring remains with identifiable
faces to tent 1.
Note locations and times.
[PEOPLE sobbing]
[DISPATCHER] Medical team 2
will arrive at Narita shortly.
Transport personnel,
report to tent 2!
[SUZAKU] Was it really her?
Did I really see here there?
And then...
[SUZAKU]
Just forget it!
She doesn't show up
in any of the data!
[LLOYD] Dug enough bodies
out of the landslide yet?
[SUZAKU] I'd like to continue
with recovery operations.
If that's possible,
Be my guest till
it's out of your system.
Consider it Princess Cornelia's
pleasure to indulge you.
[SUZAKU sighs]
Ah, Lloyd, Zero and
the Black Knights,
what are they trying to do?
What do they hope to achieve
by sacrificing all these lives?
[LLOYD] They're "Nights for
Justice," haven't you heard?
[SUZAKU]
Is this "justice"?!
[LLOYD] Hey, hey, I hope you're
not going to start spouting
some embarassing theory
about the nature of justice.
We're soldiers, after all.
[CECILE]
All set!
I replaced the
energy filler for you.
Uh, okay!
[LLOYD]
Cecile?
I checked the units,
including the Purebloods'.
And I was right, wasn't I?
[CECILE]
Yes. A radiant surge.
[LLOYD]
Rakshata!
I never thought she'd
work with our enemies.
[CECILE] Plus their pilot
was extremely skilled.
Suzaku's mental state
is so unstable now,
if we have to fight
that knightmare again...
[LLOYD]
You don't think it could win?
Against my dear Lancelot?
[TAMAKI]
This is taking too long.
When do we get there?
[sighs] Could you chill out?
You're embarassing.
Hu-- What the hell?!
[KALLEN]
We're going up?
[DRIVER]
Sorry for the inconvenience.
The master is waiting for you.
[OHGI gasps]
[TAMAKI gasps]
[OHGI]
This is... the Fuji mines?!
That is not possible!
There's no way we could be here!
It has to be Mt. Fuji! There's
only one mountain like this.
[TAMAKI] That means the
Sakuradite is right below us?!
The damn treasure that
caused this whole war!
You know what they
do to intruders here?
Execute them!
[OHGI] Their power reaches
all the way out to here?
The Kyoto Group is amazing!
[KIRIHARA]
It's repulsive!
[KALLEN, OHGI gasp]
[KIRIHARA] Mt. Fuji,
a sacred mountain
once known for its clear
water and quiet beauty...
Now, it is bent to
the empire's will,
a place of hideous violation;
a reflection of
what Japan has become.
It pains me so.
[KIRIHARA] I apologize
for not showing my face.
But, Zero, your face
is hidden as well.
Unfortunately,
I cannot allow this.
To trust you, I must
know who you are.
Therefore, you will
show me your face!
[gasps]
Please wait! Zero has
given us power and victory!
--That should--
--[KIRIHARA] Silence!
Now, which of you is Ohgi?
[OHGI]
Uh, that's me!
[KIRIHARA]
You will remove Zero's mask!
[gasps]
[KALLEN]
Ohgi!
I'm sorry, Zero,
but we need a reason
to put our faith in you, too.
So help us...
...to put our trust in you!
[TAMAKI, OHGI gasp]
[TAMAKI]
A woman?!
[OHGI]
It can't be!
[KALLEN]
It's not!
This isn't Zero!
I saw her before.
She was with Zero after Narita!
[KIRIHARA]
You there, girl, Is this true?
It is.
[KIRIHARA]
So, you are not Japanese?
Correct, clan-chief of Kyoto...
...Taizou Kirihara.
[GUARDS gasp]
Anyone who can
identify him must die!
Especially one
who is not Japanese!
Hey! Hold on!
I'm not part of this!
[ZERO]
You're soft!
And your methods and
thinking are outdated!
[KIRIHARA growls]
[ZERO]
That is why you'll never win!
Zero?
Wh-When did you--
Hold on! He can fire
at us with that remote!
Everyone, stay back!
Don't make a move!
[ZERO]
Taizou Kirihara.
Founder of Kirihara Industries
which has a monopoly
on Sakuradite mining.
Formerly a key backer
of the Kururugi regime.
However, when Japan fell,
you dodged the tribunals
by collaborating with
the colonial rulers.
Commonly known as
"Kirihara the Traitor."
In reality, you are
one of the leaders
of the "Six Houses of Kyoto,"
who support resistance
groups throughout Japan.
A double-agent. How cliché...
[MIB A]
Show some respect, you swine!
[KIRIHARA]
Stop!
[ZERO chuckles]
[ZERO] It's as you guessed
though. I... am not Japanese!
[ALL gasp]
Is he serious?!
No wonder he never
showed his face.
[KIRIHARA]
If you are not Japanese,
why do you fight for Japan?
What is it you want?!
[ZERO]
The destruction of Britannia.
[KIRIHARA] And so do you
believe that this is possible?
That you can do it?
[ZERO] I can, because I must.
I have reasons which
compel me inexorably!
[chuckles] I'm glad
I'm dealing with you.
[KIRIHARA gasps]
You!
It's been a long time.
Lord Kirihara.
[KIRIHARA]
Is it really you?
It's 8 years since that family
received you as a hostage.
[LELOUCH]
Yes.
And I appreciate you
taking care of me then.
[KIRIHARA]
If I hadn't come tonight,
were you planning to take
a messenger as hostage?
[LELOUCH]
Not at all.
I came to ask for your help;
that's all I'm seeking from you.
So, the flower planted
8 years ago has finally bloomed.
[laughs]
[TAMAKI]
Oh, I can't see 'im!
[KIRIHARA]
Ohgi!
Yes?
[KIRIHARA] This man is a
true mortal enemy of Britannia.
His face must remain
hidden for vital reasons.
I urge you to follow Zero,
and I guarantee that if you do,
we will assist you generously
with intelligence and
strategic support.
[TAMAKI sighs]
We thank you!
[LELOUCH]
I am grateful, Lord Kirihara.
Are you embarking
on the path of blood?
Indeed. If that is my destiny.
[DISASTER CENTER ANNOUNCER]
Second, fifth, seventh,
eighth, and ninth platoons,
please continue confirmation...
Yes, the spelling of
Fenette matches this one.
I'm afraid this is him.
I'm sorry you had to
learn about it like this.
It's all right...
[SOLDIER] Can you
please identify the body?
[receiver rings]
Of course it's
too late all ready.
[LELOUCH] Anyway, things
are finally moving forward.
Now, the Black Knights
will operate as I envisioned.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Ah, I'm sorry I was late.
I thought you'd already
be back home by now.
[LELOUCH]
Anyway, never mind that.
Come on, let's go someplace
to get out of the rain now.
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu, tell me...
Zero, he fights for
the weak, doesn't he?
[LELOUCH]
Wha...?
Yeah, well, that's what he says.
[SHIRLEY] Then... Then
why did he kill my father?
[gasps]
You know, my father...
was so gentle...
He never, ever hurt me...
[whmpers]
He didn't do anything wrong!
But he was buried alive...
He couldn't... breathe...
Why...?
Why did my father have to die?!
[SHIRLEY sobs]
I... don't want this...
Nooo! [wails]
[SHIRLEY sobs] Please, Lulu...
[sobbing]
[SHIRLEY]
Help me...
[LELOUCH] Yes, I understand
my actions have consequences.
I know that now, so why?
It'd be so easy to
vanish from the stage.
Just stop being Zero.
If I can keep Kirihara quiet,
I can go back to being
merely Lelouch Lamperouge.
But, even so...