[LELOUCH]
Acting at the request
of the United Federation of
Nations resolution number one
for the liberation of Japan,
the Black Knights
sent a landing force
into the Britannian Empire
colony known as Area 11.
Targeting the troops commanded
by Bismarck Waldstein,
the Knight of One, encamped
on the Kyushu coast,
the main force struck, led by
General Commander Li Xing-ke.
Using this as a diversion,
a separate detachment
of Black Knights
staged a lethal assault
on the Tokyo settlement...
But Schneizel, Prince of
Britannia, was waiting for them
with a secret weapon of mass
destruction called F.L.E.I.J.A.
At that moment, to Zero
and the Black Knights,
the very existence of
this weapon was unknown.
New orders. Black
Knights, Ikaruga fleet.
Gefjun Disturbers have
immobilized all utilities,
communications, and pre-fifth
generation Knightmares
throughout the Tokyo settlement.
The enemy's military might
has been cut in half.
Hit all major facilities
and eliminate their
ability to strike back.
We must achieve these goals
before the main forces
under Schneizel's
command arrive here.
By establishing
our defense line,
we'll isolate the
Government Bureau.
If we can seize
Viceroy Nunnally,
then victory will be ours!
Viceroy Nunnally. It's Zero!
Zero is leading an assault!
[NUNALLY gasps]
[NUNNALLY]
Zero.
Zero's on his way?!
[GINO]
Look at that smile.
Now that's more like
the real you, Kallen.
It's too bad. Your wish
won't come true.
Because I and my Tristan
fight for Britannia.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Our first priority
is to eliminate the
Gefjun Disturbers
along the railway's
circular routes.
Can we dispatch
the Lancelot for that?
That'll depend upon the current
state of Sir Kururugi's mindset.
[SCHNEIZEL chuckles]
The battlefield's not the place
for him to work out
his self-esteem issues.
[CECILE] Nina, you don't
know what you're doing!
[NINA]
If we don't act,
Zero will capture
the Tokyo settlement!
[LLOYD]
But you're not a devicer!
You may have
designed the system,
but you have no battle skills!
With the F.C.C., I can at least
defend the Government Bureau!
[SUZAKU] But are you prepared to
actually fire the F.L.E.I.J.A.?
And more importantly, are
you prepared to not fire it?
[ZERO]
Tohdoh.
Have Asahina, and Chiba
establish air supremacy.
[TOHDOH]
Roger!
That should cover everything
except their newer Knightmares,
sixth-generation and above.
Rolo!
How is the infiltration
proceeding?
Sayoko and her group
have gone on ahead of us.
We will rendezvous with them
shortly. It's all arranged.
[LELOUCH] Good. Be sure
you take Nunnally alive.
[LELOUCH]
So, you've come, Suzaku.
[SUZAKU] I'm the only one
who can make Lelouch,
make Zero, atone
for what he's done.
Listen up, Zero.
Call off your attack!
This unit is equipped with
a high-yield tactical warhead.
If I unleash it,
it will inflict catastrophic
damage beyond all known limits.
As if I'd believe anything
that you'd say! Jeremiah!
Yes, Your Majesty!
[SUZAKU] Lord Jeremiah,
is that you?! Why?!
[JEREMIAH] Suzaku Kururugi,
I owe you a debt.
I sympathize with you.
I respect you.
However, in this situation...
Loyalty trumps all!
[SUZAKU]
The Siegfried's?!
[JEREMIAH] Take this!
The storm of my loyalty!
You picked a bad time for piety.
Now!
[JEREMIAH]
Hmph.
[YUSK] The Sutherland Sieg
seems to be effective.
[RAKSHATA]
Yes, but...
[YUSK]
Huh?
[RAKSHATA] We can never
mass-produce a one-off unit
that uses the
Siegfried's system,
that's understood, right?
What I'd really like to know is
why Jeremiah's on our side now;
he's not just some
knight, you know...
That also goes for
the man once called
"the Spearhead of the Empire."
What's going on?
Why? Why am I fighting against
Royal Britannian forces?
[ZERO]
Guilford!
[gasps]
Assist Jeremiah.
Slay Suzaku Kururugi!
[GUILFORD]
But Princess, Kururugi is--!
There's no time to
explain! It's urgent!
You must trust me
and kill Kururugi!
[OFFICE WORKERS yelling]
Lord Jeremiah,
the reason I'm here
is to put an end to this battle!
Are you saying you can do it?
Are you able to dissipate
my lord's torment?
[SUZAKU] But, it shouldn't
involve the people!
Lord Guilford, too?!
Kururugi! We each serve our
royal lords! It's not personal!
[NINA]
Suzaku!
Fire the F.L.E.I.J.A.!
You can kill Zero now!
I'm sorry, Nina.
I won't unleash it.
But--!
I swear. I will stop Zero!
Excellent. Once
Suzaku's finished off,
there'll be nothing left to stop
me from taking back Nunnally.
Uh!
No one can defeat a
Knight of the Round.
No one!
Gino, thank you.
Can't you look a bit happier
when someone saves your life?
Hm? Lord Jeremiah?
So, what they said about
Orange was true, huh?
Orange, you say?
[chuckles]
That is the name of my loyalty.
[CITIZENS yelling]
This onslaught.
It's all from Schneizel
Did he anticipate my moves?
[LELOUCH]
That's right.
I'll be rendezvousing with you
a little later than I expected.
[ROLO]
Yes, I understand.
We have just cleared
all interferences
up to the 13th floor.
Don't worry. I promise,
I'll find Nunnally.
[LELOUCH]
Right. I'm counting on you.
[LELOUCH] And once
you bring back Nunnally,
I'll have no further
need for you, Rolo.
[ROLO]
Big brother.
I promised you I'd find
Nunnally and I will.
And when I do, I'll kill
her with my own hands.
I'm the only family you need.
[SAYOKO]
Master Rolo!
Emergency report from group two,
moving toward the hangars.
They say that they've
sighted priority item three.
[NUNNALLY] I won't!
I refuse to flee this way!
[LOHMEYER] The Prime Minister
has personally ordered it.
[NUNNALLY]
My brother Schneizel?
[LOHMEYER] The others
cannot leave you behind,
so if you stay,
all must stay and die.
[gasps]
Ha! You're no match
for my Gareth!
Keep dreaming! We've got
full air superiority!
We won't yield!
Oh, no... Tohdoh...
[CHIBA]
I owe you deeply, Asahina.
You've got future plans
in the works, right?
Uh, so what's our next move?
Zero ordered us not to
attack the bureau itself
until Viceroy Nunnally
has been captured alive.
[ASAHINA]
Zero, huh...
[KALLEN] They're all... They're
all fighting, while I'm...!
We'll defend it! No matter what!
Lord Guilford has
lost his sanity,
but so long as we Glaston
Knights still perform
with courage and valor,
we uphold Princess
Cornelia's honor!
[SUZAKU]
Answer me, Zero!
If you started this
battle because of me,
then let me explain...
[ZERO]
Filled with conceit as ever.
You betrayed your
father and all Japan.
'Course you betray your friends,
too. That's who you are.
Uh. What's this?
Anya? Wait!
[GINO]
Suzaku, leave Zero to Anya.
Which one do you
think is stronger?
Your shield or my
Stark Hadron cannon?
[gasps]
Even this shield can't
withstand this for very long.
Contact lost with the Shinkiro!
[OHGI]
Zero?
Apparently he's engaging in
combat with the Knight of Six!
What're your orders
for Hashimoto?
And we also have
to defend Kujuukuri.
Uh... well, I, uh...
Patch Hashimoto
over here to me.
[OHGI] Sugiyama, do we have any
units we can send to help Zero?!
Uh... just Tamaki.
[LOHMEYER]
Yes,
Viceroy Nunnally is being
put aboard the escape craft.
But until the Gefjun Disturbers
have all been deactivated...
[LOHMEYER]
Right. We can't use a Knightmare
without being targeted
by the enemy.
Yes. Understood.
Who's going to execute
Kallen Kozuki?
[UNDERLING]
Sir George.
But are you sure about this?
Viceroy Nunnally didn't--
It's for her own good,
despite her feeble
attempts to assert herself.
[gasps]
[groaning]
Sayoko!
You're looking well.
Master Rolo has gone on
to secure Miss Nunnally.
We came to give you a present,
Miss Kallen. It should fit.
I think Miss Milly's former
fiancé was behind the changes.
There seems to be a draft
instruction manual with it.
[SAYOKO]
Shall we try to get it working?
It's different, somehow...
We can't stretch our
battle lines any further.
We're already at the
breaking point now.
[SOLDIER] All Gefjun
Disturbers in Ikebukuro
and Sugamo have been destroyed.
[KANNON] Now we
can reinforce our lines
with 5th-generation
Knightmares and older.
We're also bringing
the Government Bureau's
defense system back on line.
[SCHNEIZEL] The momentum
has shifted in our favor.
[CHIBA]
The lights!
[ASAHINA]
We're out of time!
Kinoshita, haven't you
found the viceroy yet?!
The commanders have freed
Captain Kozuki, but-- Uh!
Kinoshita!
[ASAHINA]
Hey! Are you okay?!
I sent the data...
on Zero... from my system.
That's all I can... do.
[TAMAKI] What the hell?!
I can't find him!
Where's this battle
Zero is fighting?!
He's my best bud!
Just a little more.
[gasps]
[ANYA]
Again? Something is--!
The Mordred just-- Uh!
[LUCIANO]
Zero.
Face it, your Black Rebellion
is doomed to fail.
They sent another
Knight of the Round?
[LUCIANO]
Here's a question:
What do people
value most? Answer...
Their life of course!
The basic system's the same?
[SAYOKO]
We're still trying to determine
Master Zero's current position.
Shall I transfer
the I.F.F. data?
[KALLEN]
Yes, please.
Let's see... Guren S.E.I.T.E.N.
Eight. It could be.
[KALLEN]
Confirm activation.
[SAYOKO]
Activation, confirmed.
You're good to go.
Once the Guren is launched,
we'll return to our mission.
[KALLEN] Right. You take care
of the viceroy. I'll help Zero.
[SAYOKO]
Agreed. Well, then...
Guren!
[SAYOKO]
S.E.I.T.E.N. Eight Elements...
Launching!
[KALLEN]
Now launch!
[DAVID]
What the--?! Huh?
[KALLEN yells]
Father, I let you
down. Forgive me!
[CLAUDIO]
David!
Was that Kozuki?
But, that unit she's flying...
At this rate...
This shield's the only good
thing about your Knightmare.
Valkyrie squadron, don't
let him go, no matter what!
[VALKYRIES]
Yes, my lord!
[LELOUCH]
I'm in trouble!
I used up too much energy
with the Mordred!
[FUTABA]
Zero. Do you read me, Zero?!
Where are my reinforcements?!
[FUTABA]
Tamaki will be there soon.
But a picked up a fleet
over the Pacific.
[ZERO]
What about it?
[OHGI]
Zero, it's me!
It seems to be the Britannian
Emperor's flagship.
[ZERO]
What?!
He's coming to Area 11 as well?!
[SCHNEIZEL]
No.
His Majesty is not coming
to the battlefield.
What makes you
so certain of that?
Do you think he cares about
those mundane things?
The day we call "today"?
He doesn't.
[TAMAKI]
Let Zero go!
Or you'll have to deal with me,
Shinichiro Tamaki, his best bud!
Dammit! This always
happens to me!
[LELOUCH]
Yes! Now's my chance!
[gasps]
[LUCIANO] Just what
I was waiting for, Zero!
To go into attack mode,
you dropped your shield.
Now, I will take what you
value most and blow it away!
In this position,
I can't--! Nunnally!
[LUCIANO]
Hm?
Huh? They got me?
Kewell!
[KALLEN] Be careful what you
wish for, Vampire of Britannia.
Really?
Is that Kallen?
[KALLEN]
Zero. I'm here.
You're elite guard,
Kallen Kozoki, is back
on the battle line!
You thieves!
That's mine! All mine!
Not quite. I did some of
the upgrades, remember?
Oh, right.
It's actually a collaboration.
What am I talking about?!
With a capable devicer,
even at 60% output,
that unit can cut the other
Knightmares to ribbons!
[RAKSHATA] That's the
Earl of Pudding's work
and Cecile's energy
wings! How dare they?!
Altering my Guren
without my permission!
Still, now that we've got Kallen
back in the combat zone...
It will even up the battle.
[RADIO GUY 1]
Sir Bradley,
you have permission
to destroy the Guren.
[LUCIANO]
Irrelevant!
Killing is all one should
do on the battlefield!
[LUCIANO]
Ah, ah, ah!
Eleven.
Do you know the prime
truth of the battlefield?
Kill a man off the field,
and you're a criminal.
But kill him on it,
and you're a big hero.
So.
The Vampire of Britannia wants
to be a hero now, is that it?
[LUCIANO]
No, not at all.
War officially allows me to
take what people value most:
their lives.
[KALLEN] Some knight.
You're barely a scoundrel.
[LUCIANO]
And now...
[KALLEN]
And now what?
That's not gonna work.
Ah, but now I've got
you in close range.
[LUCIANO]
What?
[KALLEN] Question: What do
you value the most?
Your own pitiful life?
[LUCIANO] You think an
Eleven can threaten me?!
Send a postcard.
My life! My life is taken...
...by a lowly Eleven?!
[LUCIANO screams]
[ZERO]
Good work, Kallen!
Now get back to the Government
Bureau and get Nunnally!
[SUZAKU]
I won't let you!
[GUILFORD]
Suzaku Kururugi!
[GINO]
Easy now!
[SUZAKU]
Kallen! Stand aside!
[KALLEN]
Forget it, Suzaku!
No! Deflected?!
The Hadron blaster?
[GINO]
Kallen.
So in the end, you chose the
name Kozuki over Stadtfelt.
[KALLEN]
That's right,
which means you and
I do battle once again.
So, should I be happy
or sad about that Gino?
[GINO chuckles]
[GINO]
Why don't we just enjoy it?
Suzaku.
Let me settle things
with Kallen, okay?
[KALLEN]
It won't be easy.
[SUZAKU]
I'm sorry, Gino.
This pilot isn't
the kind of opponent
you can mess around with.
[MINASE] Tohdoh's forces
have broken through
to the enemy's command ship!
[TOHDOH yelling]
Impossible! My Gareth!
Raise all the shields
in Area Four!
[TOHDOH] We're just after
Schneizel's head!
Assume Slash and
Encircle Formation!
Tohdoh.
I'm sending you some testimony
that Kinoshita gathered.
[TOHDOH]
This is hardly the time!
Listen to it and
you'll understand.
We can't trust Commander Zero.
[TOHDOH]
Huh?
[ASAHINA] I'm going into
the government bureau
to capture Rolo.
[HINATA] Explosion detected
in section 4-I of the ship!
[OHGI]
Could it be... Chigusa?
I need to bring this
battle into close range.
Suzaku! Kallen's not the one
you need to fight! Hit Zero!
[RADIO GUY 1] Your escape route
is towards the Ikebukuro front.
[RADIO GUY 2] But there
are still Black Knights
in your fight path.
Wait till we've mopped
them up before you launch.
[SAYOKO] Master Zero,
we've found the viceroy!
I see! Excellent work!
[SAYOKO] Master Rolo
will escort us out of here
as soon as he
steals a Knightmare.
He'll have it in a moment.
Understood! Victory is
within our reach.
Kallen! Finish off Suzaku now!
He's the only thing
standing in our way!
Right!
Get out of there, Suzaku!
You can't beat that Guren!
[SUZAKU]
But, Zero--!
Ohhh!
Self-centered brat!
It's... It's too great.
The difference in
unit performance.
[KANNON]
At this rate,
we're going to lose Sir Kururugi
as well as Sir Bradley.
Fire it, Suzaku!
Use the F.L.E.I.J.A.!
No, Nina, power
is in the threat.
If we actually use it...
I can't win...
[KALLEN]
Goodbye, Suzaku.
Miss Nunnally!
Kill Suzaku! Do it!
Unleash the F.L.E.I.J.A.!
You can still save yourself!
But... if I do that...
Even if it costs me my life...
That's right.
This is redemption...
[SUZAKU]
I have to accept it.
This is where I'm
going to... to...
[LELOUCH]
Live!
I... must... live!
Is this... F.L.E.I.J.A.?
[CLAUDIO]
Fall back! All units, retreat!
[CHIBA]
Why are the Britannians running?
We have to retreat, too!
Asahina, are you reading me?!
Get out of the Government
Bureau! Asahina!
[MINAMI]
Something's wrong!
Pull the Ikaruga back
at maximum speed!
[RADIO GUY 3] You in the
Sutherland, what are you doing?
They've fired the F.L.E.I.J.A.
Fired the F.L.E.I.J.A.?
[LELOUCH] Could that be the
weapon Suzaku was talking about?
Nunnally!
General Tohdoh,
I tried to warn you!
Why did they use
the F.L.E.I.J.A. here?!
[GUILFORD] Princess,
save yourself! Princess!
Princess, you must
live! Please live!
[ALL yelping]
[LELOUCH]
Rolo...
[ROLO]
Yes, big brother?
[LELOUCH] Could you please
let me speak with Nunnally?
[ROLO]
Um. Well...
I can't reach Sayoko.
[ROLO] Listen. Big brother.
We weren't in time.
Nunnally was caught
in that flash of light.
I'm not asking you about
anything like that now.
I just wanna talk to
Nunnally, that's all.
[ROLO]
But... Nunnally is dead!
She's dead, big brother!
Don't lie to me!
[LELOUCH]
Please, Rolo.
Could you, just for a moment...
Please... let me
speak with Nunnally.