The world lies!
Thou shalt not commit murder!
Thou shalt not
bear false witness!
Thou shall not cheat!
Thou shall not steal!
Thou shalt not covet
they neighbor's wife!
All of these are lies!
Mere illusion, nothing more!
They don't want to be killed!
They don't want to be robbed!
Using the twin lies of
"justice" and "morality,"
the weak are endeavoring
to protect themselves!
But the first truth is that
the strong devour the weak!
So let us feed
Upon people! Upon wealth!
Upon riches and power!
We of Britannia shall feast
upon the raw flesh
of the world itself!
We must crush this deception
and bring forth the truth!
ALL HAIL BRITANNIA!
[SOLDIERS] All hail Britiannia!
All hail Britiannia!
[gasps]
You looked like you
were having a nightmare.
A nightmare...
[ROLO] Did something
happen yesterday?
No, not really.
Uh, Rolo.
Did I happen to say anything?
[ROLO]
Huh?
[LELOUCH gasps]
Nunnally...
[gasps]
[ROLO]
No, Lelouch.
You didn't say one thing.
Nothing at all.
I see.
[LELOUCH]
The world Nunnally desires.
The future Nunnally has chosen.
But that leaves me, leaves Zero,
standing in the way.
My sister's safety
has been guaranteed.
She has the Britannian
military forces
to protect her, and Suzaku, too.
He may be my worst enemy,
but I trust him to
do at least that.
Yes. As I had once
hoped he would.
And even after I can no
longer safeguard Nunnally.
[SHIRLEY]
Look at this!
It says this temple was
built a thousand years ago!
That's great. Have you
seen the water pistols?
I got one for everyone,
but I can't find 'em.
Hey, what's all
this stuff, Prez?
[MILLY]
Some nets, candles, wigs,
fireworks, and a tambourine.
Uh... So are those
for our class trip?
Just leave it to me!
'This'll be my
second time, y'know!
Right...Uh?
[SHIRLEY, RIVALZ]
Hm? Uh...
What's wrong, Lulu?
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
You just seem sort of down.
No, I'm fine.
Can't sleep 'cuz
you're thinking about
how much fun the trip'll be?
You're correct.
Yeah, I'm excited about it.
Lulu, you're just
like a little boy.
Heh...Huh?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Attention all students.
The inauguration speech of
the new viceroy of Area 11
is about to begin.
Please assemble
in the auditorium.
[NUNNALLY]
How do you do, everyone?
I am Nunnally vi Britannia
of the royal family,
87th in line to
the imperial throne.
Due to the unfortunate,
untimely loss of
Duke Calares recently,
I shall be assuming
the viceroyship
of Area 11 in his place.
I am physically
challenged in that
I am unable to either
see or walk. Therefore...
But she's so young. How could
that girl be a viceroy?
She's a royal princess!
[NUNNALLY]
...Please, help me to help you.
She wants some help, hm?
This'll screw up things.
[NUNNALLY]
I realize this is unexpected,
but I'd like each one of you
to cooperate with me on this.
Huh?
As your new Viceroy,
I wish to again create the
Specially Administrated
Zone of Japan.
[gasps]
That's absurd!
I can't believe she would
even mention the name!
[NUNNALLY]
In the Special Zone,
Britannians and Numbers
would have equal status.
Elevens will be allowed
to safely call themselves
Japanese once again.
She just said Japanese!
Are they trying to trick us?
She has Suzaku Kururugi.
He's Japanese, so he
should be on our side.
[ELEVEN 5]
Princess Massacre's knight!
He's the traitor who shot Zero!
[NUNNALLY] Although a
tragic misunderstanding
occurred in the Special Zone,
I do not believe
that the attempt to establish
the zone was a mistake.
We need a gentler world.
[gasps]
And those of you in
the Black Knights,
I ask you to please participate
in the Special Zone.
What?!
Not again!
Never again.
[NUNNALLY] ...and admit to
the mistakes that we've made,
then we can take the
first positive steps
--to setting things right.
--[ROLO] Huh?
[NUNNALLY] I believe
this with all my heart.
[CROWD murmurs]
[SUZAKU]
You surprised me, Nunnally.
You're trying to create the
Japan Special Zone, again.
Suzaku, what Euphy tried to do,
I mean before the disaster
happened, wasn't wrong, was it?
[SUZAKU]
No.
I can assure you it wasn't
Euphy who was wrong.
[NUNNALLY]
Hm.
[TRAIN P.A.] Passengers
transferring to the
express line,
please wait on platform 3.
[gasps]
[TRAIN P.A.] Those transferring
to the Sen-Kyou line,
please change at
the next station.
The local train will be
stopping at platform number 5.
[LELOUCH]
They're not needed any more.
Neither Zero...or my battle.
Uh?
[phone ringing]
--[phone clicks]
--[KALLEN gasps]
[TAMAKI]
Heh-heh!
That kid viceroy
just want to repeat
what Princess Massacre
Euphemia did!
[OHGI] No Japanese person
would ever take part in it.
[TAMAKI] After luring
them in with sugary words
and then slaughtering them?
Not a chance!
So, what're we
gonna do, then?
[TAMAKI] Have a showdown
with the Britannians!
How do we do that
when the only
knightmare we have
left is one Guren?
[TAMAKI] We'll just go
to Zero, of course, and--
[KAGUYA]
That's right!
[ALL]
Huh?
[KALLEN]
Lady Kaguya!
I'm in agreement
with Tamaki, however...
Why isn't Master Zero here?
Considering his new
wife awaits him eagerly.
In fact, he failed to
write me even once
while I was away in the
Chinese Federation!
Maybe he dumped you
for someone else!
[OHGI gasps]
Ah! Don't be ridiculous!
It's not true!
Seriously, it's not!
That doesn't
matter at all to me.
[KALLEN]
Huh?
The greatest men succumb
to feminine charm.
Grown up men have
basic physical needs.
Lady Kaguya,
what're you saying?!
[C.C.]
Thank goodness.
You're a lot more
generous than you seem.
I so appreciate you
keeping him company while
I was away. Thank you.
[C.C.]
Hm. No need to thank me.
Here, you as well, Kallen.
Uh?! I...!
We three who support
Master Zero! Oh?
That makes us three ladies
of his court, doesn't it?
[KALLEN, C.C.]
His court?
Salutations and greetings! Hm?
Where's Suzaku?
[CECILE]
He refused to stay here.
He went after the Black Knights.
We were right in the middle
of his complete physical, too.
[LLOYD]
Well, that's typical of our boy.
I'm not surprised.
[GUILFORD]
Uh...?
We have to perfect
the Conquista, right?
[LLOYD]
Ugh.
So, how is it?
I mixed peanut
butter with turmeric sugar
and wasabi paste,
then spread it on rye bread!
[LLOYD groans]
That's typical of you!
[LELOUCH]
Even though...
Even though I've been
doing all this up until now
for Nunnally's sake...
[CONDUCTOR]
Huh?
How do you do, everyone?
[LELOUCH gasps]
I am Nunnally vi Britannia
of the royal family,
87th in line to the
imperial throne.
Due to the unfortunate,
untimely loss of Duke
Calares recently,
I shall be assuming...
What's your problem?!
Watch it!
[NUNNALLY]
...In his place.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[WORKER MNS]
Hey!
[LELOUCH gasps]
I'm finished!
[SUZAKU] Nunnally may have
realized that I lied to her.
Even so, she said she wants
to carry on Euphie's wishes.
And for that, I'll...
[THUG A] We told you
money first, didn't we?
[THUG B] Cough it up,
ya stinkin' deadbeat!
[THUG C]
Loser!
[ELEVEN VICTIM]
Stop it, please!
Why are you doing this?
Aren't you guys
Elevens like me?!
[KOLCHAK]
Bring the cash next time.
If you want this stuff.
[KOLCHAK]
Hm?
[THUG]
A Britannian?
[THUG D]
A student?
Japanese feeding
on other Japanese.
What a picture.
But even worse than that,
they commit petty
crimes for a Britannian.
Ha! Did you call them Japanese?
[THUG A] We don't need
sympathy from any Britannians!
[THUG C]
We call ourselves Elevens.
And a school boy
shouldn't complain
about the work we do!
Yes, I use these gentlemen
to do my bidding,
but only with their consent.
My dear student.
Don't touch me! You scum!
Why you--!
Now get on the ground
and do push-ups!
As you like.
[THUGS gasp]
[THUG D] Mr. Kolchak,
what are you doing?!
And why don't you
do some dancing?
[THUG D]
Whoa! Yeah, baby!
Do squats!
Start howling!
Applaud!
[ALL shattering]
[LELOUCH laughs]
[C.C.] It's really makes
no difference at all
if he doesn't come back here.
The one single thing
that's important to me
is that he remains alive.
Oh, please.
The simplest solution would
be for him to stop being Zero.
I know. Not a very
romantic story, is it?
Still, at this rate,
the Black Knights
are over, they're history.
Yes. Zero exists
for Nunnally's sake.
That's what
Lelouch said, Marianne.
[MILLY sighs]
Where's Lelouch?
Dunno. What is up with that guy?
[KALLEN]
I figured you'd come here.
[gasps]
Where Zero was born.
You started it here,
this is where it all began.
[KALLEN] Lelouch, I want
to tell you something.
[gasps]
[KALLEN]
Is that--?!
[LELOUCH]
Refrain.
You're familiar
with it, aren't you?
Brings back memories
of the good old days.
Don't give me that crap!
[gasps]
[KALLEN grunts]
So what if you
failed this time?!
Can't you come up with
another plan and get it back?!
Just give us orders
like you always do!
Should I use
my Knightmare?
Or maybe play decoy?
Tell me! I'll do
whatever you say!
All right, then.
You can console me.
[gasps]
There are things a woman
can do for that, right?
[KALLEN gasps]
[KALLEN]
No!
[LELOUCH gasps]
Snap out of it, Lelouch!
You're Zero now!
You have an obligation!
You've got to live up to the
dreams you once gave us all!
So please, keep fooling us
until you no longer can!
We need you to be Zero this
time with all of your heart.
Play your role like you mean it!
[KALLEN whimpers]
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH sighs]
[LELOUCH]
Rolo.
[KALLEN huffs]
[LELOUCH] That's right, you're
supposed to keep an eye on me.
I had forgotten.
[ROLO] Then why not...
forget about them?
[LELOUCH]
Hm.
[ROLO] All the heavy burdens
that just weigh you down.
Zero. The Black Knights.
And Nunnally...
[LELOUCH] You're wrong!
Nunnally isn't a--
For Nunnally's sake, as well.
[gasps]
[ROLO] If Zero vanishes, then
peace will come to Area 11.
Lelouch, you can go back
to being an ordinary
student again and be happy.
[LELOUCH]
But...
[ROLO] Is there
something wrong with that?
Wanting happiness isn't a crime.
No one would have to be hurt.
Look, we still have time
to undo what's been done!
[LELOUCH gasps]
It's all right. I'll never
abandon you, I promise.
I'll stay with you as your
brother forever, Lelouch.
[EMPEROR]
Tell me, Nunnally,
why would you request this?
Why did you want to
be viceroy of Area 11
after learning
Zero had returned?
Because my entire life,
I have lived under
the protection of my
big brother, Lelouch.
I may not know where
he is at this moment,
but I'm sure that he's out
there watching me at every turn.
Therefore, I don't want to
make an embarrassing
decision as viceroy while
he's looking over my shoulder!
[C.C.] That mask is
heavier than it looks.
The wearer bears a fate.
Not just of the Japanese people,
but that of the world.
Yes. But somebody has to--
[SUZAKU]
This is the Britannian military.
Your ship's registry and
stated course are erroneous.
Heave to at once!
We will now conduct
a forced inspection!
[KALLEN]
They found us?!
It appears so.
[SUZAKU]
Everyone aboard is ordered
to disarm and line
up on the deck.
You have ten minutes to
comply with our order!
[LELOUCH]
That's right.
Everybody's gone
on the school trip.
[ROLO]
Should we go after them?
[LELOUCH]
No.
An empty birdcage suits
me just fine for now.
[LELOUCH, ROLO]
Huh?
Who's firing?
[LELOUCH panting]
Hi! Welcome back, Lulu!
Light some off, too, Lelouch.
We have plenty left
over from the festival.
Why are you...?
What about the school trip?
[grunts] We couldn't
leave you here crying
while we three went and had fun.
Cuz' the important
thing about vacations
isn't where you spend them,
it's all about who
you spend them with.
[SHIRLEY]
Exactly!
[gasps]
Why, that's a...
[SHIRLEY]
Hm? Oh, you mean this?
These are supposed to make
your wishes come true,
so I made one.
[gasps]
[SHIRLEY]
For the life of me,
I can't remember who taught
me how to make them, though.
And what did you wish for?
It's already coming true.
Well, part of it.
I wanted to set off
fireworks with everyone.
Everyone?
For Nina, Kallen...
... and Suzaku.
It goes without
saying, you and Rolo.
[gasps]
And because I only
folded one crane,
you were the only
one who showed up!
[LELOUCH] A long time ago,
Nunnally, Suzaku,
and I talked about something.
We wondered what
happiness would look like
if we could give
it a physical form.
If I'm not mistaken,
I think it was Suzaku
who said that the shape
of happiness might
resemble glass.
His reasoning made sense.
He said that even though
you don't usually notice it,
it's still definitely there.
You merely have to change
your point of view slightly,
and then that glass will sparkle
when it reflects the light.
I doubt that anything else
could argue its own
existence more eloquently.
[NUNNALLY] They say if you
fold a thousand of these cranes,
your wish'll come true.
What about you?
Do you wish for anything?
[NUNNALLY]
Hmm...
I wish the world was
a gentler place.
[LELOUCH] That's right.
A gentle world is this close.
Even if we were clouded
by phony memories,
like transparent glass.
[LELOUCH]
Always. Always. Always.
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu?
[RIVALZ]
What're you crying for?
[gasps]
Lelouch, are you really moved
that much by our friendship?
You do have a sweet side!
No, you're wrong!
I-It's nothing like that at all.
[ALL giggle]
[LELOUCH]
Everyone?
[ALL]
Hm?
I'll launch fireworks
with you again some day.
We will.
We'll do it together,
right here.
I promise.
[ALL sigh]
[LELOUCH] Yes, as a matter
of fact... my battle--
It isn't just about
Nunnally any more.
[COMM. VOICE 1]
It's time.
Commence firing.
[TOHDOH]
Here it comes!
Blow the tanker!
That'll scramble the sonar.
30 degrees down trim!
Engines, crash dive!
Any contact with Zero yet?
[CHIBA]
Still no response, sir.
We'll assume they're
trying to escape underwater.
Send out the Portmans.
Confirming sonar!
The engine noise sounds
like submersibles!
Dive us down.
If they discover us, we're done.
Fire ASROCs!
[CREW grunting]
Do not panic.
They're guessing where we are.
[PILOT A] Encircle the area
centering on point theta!
We'll smoke the enemy out!
[MALE CREWMAN screams]
[FEMALE CREWMAN]
What?!
All sections report leaks!
Your orders?!
If we move,
then they'll find us.
We hold out.
What?! But--
[ 05 SUB CREW]
[ALL grunting]
We're all gonna die!
[ZERO]
Q-1, do you read me? Q-1!
That voice...
[grunts]
Zero!
[ZERO] Your instructions:
50 degrees down trim.
Head for point L-14.
Crash dive, full ahead!
Ha! He made it!
Finally! Took him long enough!
[giggles]
Continue depth charge drop.
Maintain encirclement!
Fire all torpedoes to
detonate dead ahead!
Set detonators for 40 seconds.
Straight in front of us?
There's no enemy there!
Let's try firing them!
[ALL]
Huh?!
What other choice do we have?
We've got to trust him!
Set detonators,
then launch all
torpedoes straight ahead!
[SONAR MAN]
Torpedo launch confirmed.
Enemy location, tracked.
[SUZAKU]
They're at point L-14.
Focus fire on that point!
If they surface,
I'll capture them myself!
[PORTMAN PILOT A]
Salamander to Blue Dolphin.
Changing firing
angle toward point.
Dispatch to Portman
expansion zone.
[PORTMAN PILOT B]
Roger that.
Tightening up the dragnet.
Make sure your
target lock's good.
[PORTMAN PILOT A] Salamander
confirming target acquired.
Rotating depth
charge launch tubes.
Ready to fire!
[ZERO]
Once the anchors are secure,
all hands, brace for shock!
[ALL grunt]
[ALL scream]
It's air?!
[RAKSHATA]
Now I see!
That's methane hydrate!
[PORTMAN PILOT B]
What the--?!
[PORTMAN PILOT C]
Our buoyancy!
[PORTMAN PILOT D]
Sir Kururugi! Bubbles!
[PORTMAN PILOT D screams]
What the--?!
[DECK CAPTAIN]
H-Helm!
[DECK ADJUTANT]
No good! We're capsizing!
How could...?!
[SUZAKU]
They caused giant bubbles
to rise from the sea floor?!
[GINO]
Suzaku, look at this!
It's beyond calling
for reinforcements!
Take remaining units and
go after the Black Knights!
[COMM VOICE 2]
It's Zero!
Zero's heading right for me!
Master Zero!
So this...
This is your answer to me?!
[ZERO]
Don't shoot!
Shoot me, and you'll be
disobeying your lady's orders.
What?!
[ZERO] I hereby accept
the offer extended by
Viceroy Nunnally! Yes, I will
join the Japan Special Zone.
[gasps]
He wouldn't!
Zero's surrendering to them?
But he can't!
Are you serious?
[ZERO]
Zero orders you!
All members of
the Black Knights!
You shall participate
willingly in the Special Zone!
[LELOUCH]
Perhaps you're laughing.
Perhaps you're enjoying it.
However, that isn't the truth.
I am the only one
who knows the tragedy
that's hidden behind your smile.
If but one person
is aware of the truth
and holds the
power to save you...
Yes...
I must oppose the kind
of rule called "peace."
Oppose the system
that looks down upon us,
despises us,
and treats us like toys.
In the name of Zero...