[LELOUCH]
The world continues moving on,
thanks to miracles
which Zero has performed.
The world is being reborn,
thanks to actions
which Zero has taken.
Yes... the world is
moving to the next stage,
as it should.
Against conflicting emotions,
Zero must carry on,
for the hands which mark time
cannot be stopped.
[GUILFORD]
I came alone, as I promised.
Now, what's the meaning
of this, Jeremiah?
If you have information on
Princess Cornelia's whereabouts,
then why do you need to
tell it only to me in secret?
[RADIO] The Black Knights are
approaching the Kagoshima coast.
But rest assured,
there's no need to worry.
Under the command
of Lord Waldstein,
the Knight of One,
we Britannians shall--
[COMMANDER 1] This is already
Britannian territory!
Don't let a
single soldier land here!
[XING-KE] The enemy
has fallen for our plan!
They'll be
shorthanded in the south,
so dispatch our
landing forces ashore!
[COMMANDER 2]
Enemy headed for Yamaguchi!
[COMMANDER 3]
Garcia team wiped out!
[OFFICER 1]
Damn the Black Knights!
How did they amass
this strength?!
[OFFICER 2]
We thought we could hold
our territorial defense line,
but after what Xing-ke did to us
in the Battle
of the East China Sea--
All right, don't panic!
As long as we're
able to defend Area 11,
all the imperial armies
led by Prince Odysseus
and the other
royal family members
can rush into the
U.F.N. territories.
The remaining Knights
of the Round
are deployed on the
front line, as well.
[KAGUYA]
Or, to put it another way,
if Japan is liberated, the other
colony areas of Britannia
will spring into action
one after another,
which would redefine
the map of the world!
In summation...
...it's the decisive battle.
[LELOUCH] Has it really
been eight years?
Eight years since Nunnally
and I were left on our own
at the Kururugi shrine.
And there...
[SUZAKU] How do you
like that, you stupid Brit?!
[LELOUCH] That was
where we first met Suzaku.
[SUZAKU] I don't need a reason
to save who I want to save
or do what I want to do!
[LELOUCH]
You always were stubborn.
But of course...
that was the reason.
The reason you became the first
and only real friend I ever had.
[LELOUCH]
And that's why...
Why I think I'll take
a chance on you, Suzaku.
If you can accept me,
then perhaps...
[laughing]
This will hardly do for me!
Why such meager offerings?
[PILOT 1]
The Vampire of Britannia!
[PILOT 2] Let's hit him
at the same time!
[PILOT 3]
Right!
[PILOT 4]
Six-Way Charge attack!
[LUCIANO]
Hah!
Wha--What the--?!
[LUCIANO] Question:
"What do people value most?"
Stop it! Please!
[LUCIANO]
That's right! Your own life!
Please, no...!
[laughing]
Our left wing is crumbling,
Master Xing-ke!
It's one Knightmare
with unique breakthrough power.
Dispatch Indira's
team for support.
Have left-wing
teams fall back at once.
Decoy and isolate enemy unit!
[XIANG-LIN]
Roger!
As far as I'm aware,
Prince Schneizel
ought to be staying in Tokyo.
[SCHNEIZEL]
There's nothing to fear.
The Knight of One,
the strongest in the empire,
is in Kyushu.
If we can just ride this out
and remain anchored in Tokyo,
this will only look like minor
trouble to foreign countries.
[ALL]
Yes, Your Highness!
[SCHNEIZEL]
It'll be all right, Nunna.
I expect this war
will be over soon.
I have a knack for
reading these situations.
[SPEAKER]
The Savage Valkyrie Squadron
repelled the ambush
troops from Nagasaki.
[SPEAKER 2] Now dispatching
[SPEAKER 3] Send Sir Morrey
to the front as back-up.
[SPEAKER 4]
Sir Karim, fall back,
rendezvous with Sir Lasceaux...
It looks as if
the enemy offensive
is losing steam,
and if you join the battle,
you'll surely finish this
with one blow, Lord Waldstein!
You think so?
[MECHANIC]
Huh?
[BISMARCK]
This attack is far too weak
for one of Zero's
trademark strategies.
[ATC]
Prepare to launch.
Special equipment unit one,
provide support.
Galahad, launch!
[SUZAKU]
You came alone?
[LELOUCH]
I promised I would.
[SUZAKU] You have a lot
of nerve coming here.
[LELOUCH] According to
this particular situation,
there are 31 routes I can take.
Especially with
Britannia being so loose
with the routes relating
to the royal family--
[SUZAKU] That's not
what I meant, Lelouch.
Showing your face
in front of me,
that's what took nerves.
Not your own daring.
But you promised?
I have no reason to believe any
of your promises at this point.
[LELOUCH]
Then explain to me.
Why did you come here
alone as well?
After what you did?
[SUZAKU]
You want to know?
I'm fed up with lying.
I've had to lie to Nunnally.
Just the way you have.
That's the worst thing.
Some friend you were.
You've been
betraying me all along!
Not just me, either,
but everyone on the
student council, too.
And even Nunnally.
And don't forget Euphy!
[ASAHINA] Are you sure
about this, Tohdoh?
We just wait here?
[TOHDOH] We still haven't
received word from Zero.
[CHIBA] But now that
the Knights of the Round
have joined the battle,
even General Commander
Xing-ke is no match.
Have faith in Zero.
How can we,
after he brought Orange
and that Rolo person
into our ranks
without conferring
with us first?
Don't you feel
that he's keeping
too many secrets from us?
Like when he took Kinoshita
on that secret mission!
We need Zero's abilities
now more than ever.
Haven't we already discussed
this many times with Ohgi
as well as the others?
[ASAHINA] So...
what if Japan is liberated?
[CHIBA]
Right. What happens then?
[TOHDOH] Rakshata,
where are Ohgi and Diethard?
[RAKSHATA]
Don't know.
[OHGI] All right, just what
are you trying to achieve
by threatening me, Diethard?
[DIETHARD]
Threaten you? Oh, no.
I'm simply asking you
to continue working
as a member of the
Black Knights as you have been.
[OHGI]
What do you mean by that?
[DIETHARD] Look, I'm only saying
that I don't want you
to be any trouble
to Zero, that's all.
[OHGI] Why? There are plenty
of people who can replace me.
[DIETHARD] You're valuable
for the simple reason
that you're a man
of ordinary character.
[OHGI]
Hm?
[DIETHARD] Organizations need
more than brilliant leadership
and star players
in order to succeed.
[SUZAKU]
I need to know.
Did you use your Geass
power on Euphy? Be honest.
Yes.
[SUZAKU] You caused her
to massacre the Japanese?
I ordered her to do it.
[SUZAKU] Why would you
use your Geass like that?!
Answer me!
[LELOUCH]
To motivate the Japanese people.
If the Specially
Administrated Zone of Japan
had been established,
the Black Knights
would have collapsed.
[SUZAKU]
And Shirley's death?
[LELOUCH]
Also my fault.
You aren't even human,
you know that?
Shirley and Euphy...
Were both of them nothing more
than pawns for your ambitions?
Yes, that's right.
So all the sin is
mine alone to shoulder.
My little sister
had nothing to do with it!
Why, you coward!
How could you use
Nunnally like that?!
Suzaku... I'm sorry.
And he always
played Santa Claus for me.
Big brother would
dress up like him
and even stuff
pillows under his shirt.
[KALLEN] The face of
the kind older brother
and the mask of Zero...
Which is the real Lelouch?
[GINO]
Huh? He isn't here, either?
[GINO] By any chance,
have you seen Suzaku?
[KALLEN]
No. I doubt he'd come here.
[XING-KE] Send Hong's unit
into the right wing,
and get ready
for the second charge!
You are the commander,
are you not, sir?
Came to crush the head
of the snake, have you?!
[XING-KE]
It's a basic tactic.
[BISMARCK]
Hmph.
Behold, Excalibur!
The holy sword
bestowed upon me
by His Majesty himself!
[LELOUCH]
For the first time in my life,
I'm bowing down
to another person.
Shame and honor
mean nothing to me.
All I want is this,
and my Geass be damned!
Just please!
You have to save Nunnally!
I beg of you--
[LELOUCH groans]
After everything you've done,
you really think
this is sufficient?!
You believe that
some bowing and begging
is enough to get me
to forgive you?!
[LELOUCH] No, of course I don't,
but it's all I've got!
I have nothing else
left to offer!
And you're the
only person in the world
who can save my sister now!
So you believe...
...that I'll just ignore
the past and forgive you?
That everyone is
going to forgive you?!
The people you've tricked?
The people who died
thanks to you?
And what about Euphy?!
You want to apologize?!
Then bring Euphy
back to life! Right now!
I want to see you save
the world with all your malice!
[SUZAKU]
Right now!
You're Zero,
the miracle worker, aren't you?!
[LELOUCH]
I've performed no miracles.
It's all been calculation
and stage production.
The mask they call Zero
is a symbol!
Just a device
that lets me tell lies!
[SUZAKU]
A device?
You don't really expect me
to buy that excuse, do you?!
If you're going to tell a lie,
then keep it up
till the very end!
I can't go back to the past!
It's not a choice!
You know I can't undo
what's already been done!
Lelouch, you will answer me!
[SUZAKU] Why did you
use your Geass on me
to make me want to live?
[SUZAKU]
Why?!
[SUZAKU] The Geass you used
on me that drives me to live
has corrupted my convictions.
Why would you
put such a curse me?!
[LELOUCH] I only did it
because I wanted to survive.
[SUZAKU] And why did you
save me when I was accused
of Prince Clovis' murder?
[LELOUCH] I wanted to make the
Japanese trust me, that's all.
[SUZAKU] Why did you save
the student council members
from the hotel jacking?!
[LELOUCH]
Because I thought it presented
an ideal opportunity
for the Black Knights' debut.
[SUZAKU]
The look in his eyes...
I know that look.
The look of torment that
comes from bottling up a lie.
That's why I joined
the Britannian army.
For redemption.
So that the tragedy
wouldn't repeat itself.
[SUZAKU]
You're lying, aren't you?
Lelouch...
There's only one way to
redeem yourself for those lies.
Turn your falsehoods
into the truth.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[SUZAKU]
You told the world a lie
when you proclaimed that you
were a knight for justice.
Why don't you
live up to that lie
by trying to become
a true knight for justice?
Then you'll have
to keep the lie going.
To the very end.
But how... how could I do that?
By putting an end to this war.
You are Zero.
This job--only Zero can do it.
It's within your power.
Bring peace and happiness
to the world.
If you do that,
I'll save Nunnally.
You will? You'll save her?
[SUZAKU]
But we'll work together.
One more time, for her sake.
I'm grateful.
The two of us together...
We can accomplish anything.
[SUZAKU]
Wh-What the...?!
[CLAUDIO]
Hold it right there, Zero!
We've already uncovered
your true identity!
[BRIT 1] Are you
all right, Sir Kururugi?!
[BRIT 2]
Please step back!
Suzaku...!
You set me up from the start!
No, wait!
You've done a great
deed here, Sir Kururugi.
Excellent work.
You've managed to
bring this war to an end.
[LELOUCH]
I see...
You planned to
sell me out again!
You betrayed me, Suzaku...
You betrayed me!
[GINO] It's because Suzaku's
been acting so weird lately.
I thought this might help
to take his mind off things
for a while.
[KALLEN] This was in
the student council room?
[GINO]
Yeah.
I found it hidden
deep in a locker,
like it was something valuable.
There are a few photos missing
here and there, though.
Ones of you, too.
But I suppose he
couldn't leave evidence
that shows him palling
around with a terrorist!
Yet everyone appears... well...
[KALLEN]
That's right. He...
[GINO]
He can look like that too, huh?
[KALLEN]
Huh?
[GINO] I've never seen
Suzaku smile like that.
He's so happy.
[KALLEN]
Good for him.
Hey, look.
[KALLEN]
What?
I understand that you're a
Britannian-Eleven
half-breed, right?
[GINO] If you chose the name
Stadtfelt instead of Kouzuki,
you could very well have
a good life, couldn't you?
Even become one of
the Knights of the Round
if you have such ambitions.
[KALLEN]
Is this going somewhere?
What I mean, is wouldn't
you like to come back
over to our side, Kallen?
[PILOT]
Sir Bradley, please stop!
[LUCIANO]
Oh, buck up!
You've taken so many hits,
you're only going
to crash anyway.
So, in light of that,
I, Luciano,
will use your plight
to our advantage!
And settle it in one blow!
[XIANG-LIN] He's using one of
his own ships as a weapon?!
Fall back at
full speed while firing!
[OPERATOR] It's no use!
We'll never make it!
[BISMARCK] Where do you
think you're going?
Ah... You show skill!
[XING-KE]
Good! From this position...!
[BISMARCK]
Nicely done. Good form.
You parried my sword thrust
then swiftly attacked
in the follow-through.
You, the one named Xing-ke.
The rumors of your prowess
are evidently true.
General Commander Xing-ke
appears to be wounded!
[FUTABA]
Da Long Dan, withdrawing!
Chief of staff Zhou Xiang-Lin
now assuming
operational command.
Zero, what's taking so long?!
I can't believe Zero's identity
is that of a student!
[LELOUCH]
Guilford!
[SCHNEIZEL]
How sad.
Zero, killer of royalty.
It's tragic that
it would turn out to be you.
My own younger brother.
Your brother...!
[SCHNEIZEL] However, Lelouch,
I'm willing to intercede
with His Majesty on your behalf.
You realize, of course,
that you can't simply be excused
for the crimes you've committed,
but your life may yet be spared.
[LELOUCH] So you think
you can take pity on me?!
[SUZAKU]
Y-You mean...
[KANON]
Yes.
This was all done under orders
from Prince Schneizel.
[KANON]
He figured that following you
would ultimately
lead us to Zero.
You see, His Highness
was well aware
of the fact that you and Zero
shared an unusual relationship.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Lelouch, even now,
I do still consider
myself your brother.
I carry no grudge.
Can you believe me
when I say this?
And why should I?
[SCHNEIZEL]
You should trust your brother.
I would love to
be able to, brother.
Unfortunately, I'm done with
trusting anyone or anything.
Because friendship
only leads to betrayal.
[LELOUCH]
Lord Guilford.
Identify yourself!
You're not Orange!
[LELOUCH] Wait. I just have
a request to ask of you.
Yes, all right, then.
What is it you want
me to do for you?
[LELOUCH]
Oh, it's quite simple, really.
Whenever you see me
assume this pose...
You will recognize
and acknowledge me
as Princess Cornelia.
And then...
P-Princess Cornelia!
Is that you?!
Guilford, my knight, it is I!
You must rescue me!
[GUILFORD]
Yes... Your Highness!
Very good, Guilford.
I'm pleased that you noticed it!
Stop it, Lord Guilford!
What are you doing?!
[GUILFORD]
Have you gone mad?!
How dare you hold
her captive like that?!
Even Lord Guilford
has been affected.
Now I suppose I have no choice
but to believe in this power.
[GUILFORD] Princess,
we need to withdraw for now!
Lelouch, no!
[LELOUCH] I bid you farewell,
my first and last friend.
Lelouch! Come back!
[CECILE]
Lloyd! I can't believe it!
Lord Guilford has
turned into a traitor!
[NINA]
Is it true?!
We're just standing by?
[LLOYD]
Mm-hmm.
Prince Schneizel ordered us to,
so we're complying.
[NINA] I had heard that
Zero made an appearance, but...
[CECILE] We haven't
been told anything yet.
But something critical
was disclosed is my suspicion.
[SUZAKU]
I need to know.
Did you use your
Geass power on Euphy?
Be honest.
Sir Kururugi,
would you happen to know
the reason why Lord Guilford
would suddenly
betray us like this?
As well as why you
behaved the way you did
on Kamine Island that time?
Shouldn't we be pursuing
Zero right now, sir?
There's some
important information we need
before we can pursue him.
Information that only
you know, Sir Kururugi.
[OPERATOR 1]
Wired C response, confirmed.
[OPERATOR 2]
Synchronization, achieved.
[OPERATOR 3]
Ragnarok backup, reinitializing.
Guilford,
we'll proceed on course
to the Tokyo settlement.
[GUILFORD]
Yes, Your Highness.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Suzaku Kururugi!
Who are you? A Japanese?
An honorary Britannian?
A Knight of Seven?
Or are you the son
of a Prime Minister?
The son of Genbu Kururugi?
Lelouch's friend?
Euphemia's knight?
Unless you tell us right now
what we need to know,
there are going to be
more unnecessary casualties
and destruction
before it's over.
Just how long?
How long will you allow this sad
chain of events to continue?
[CAPTAIN]
Don't worry.
The modifications to
the settlement's structure
are complete.
Zero won't be able to collapse
it the way he did before.
[COMMANDER]
We have word. It's Zero.
[CAPTAIN]
So, the fool has come.
Prepare to attack!
You're cleared to shoot
down the Vincent as well!
[LELOUCH] Don't assume
that I was portraying
the role of a student in the
settlement without reason!
Tokyo settlement, I'll bring
you to a halt right now!
[BRIT CAPTAIN]
Fire!
What?!
My... My energy filler!
[BRIT SOLDIER B]
A Gefijun Disturber?!
And so, that situation
will lead us to--Hm?
[MILLY gasps]
[MILLY]
Sorry, viewers,
but it seems that
the power's gone out
here in the studio.
Um, are we still broadcasting?
[LELOUCH] All tasks
at hand have been cleared.
Tohdoh!
Acknowledged! Now
commencing Seventh Operation!
Raise the Ikaruga!
[HINATA]
Ikaruga surfacing!
[FUTABA] All fleet units,
surface at will!
Ohgi, right now, you realize--
Yes, I'm aware!
[TOHDOH] The main fleet
will stay on course
through Tokyo Bay,
break through into
the Tokyo settlement,
and rendezvous with Zero!
[MINASE]
All hands, battle stations!
All right, let's do this!
This battle...
...will be ours!
[JEREMIAH]
Now I shall prove my loyalty!
For Prince Lelouch
and Princess Nunnally!
[BISMARCK] What? The Black
Knights are in Tokyo Bay?!
Lord Waldstein,
I request that you dispatch
me and my
Savage Valkyrie Squadron!
You mean to the
Tokyo settlement?
Do you really want to
burnish your record that badly?
[LUCIANO]
No.
I merely take uncommon
pleasure in destroying them.
[LELOUCH] Rolo,
how are things on your end?
Fine.
We're beginning
the operation right now.
We'll make our way
to Nunnally first thing.
[LELOUCH]
Good. I'm counting on you, Rolo.
That's right.
I was grossly mistaken.
I was wrong to think that
I could depend on sympathy.
Cold and callous,
that's the prescription.
Unless I keep myself perfectly
in this frame of mind,
I won't be able
to take Nunnally back!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Lelouch...
I thought something
strange had been going on
ever since our brother
Clovis was killed.
But now I understand.
I understand everything.
But now...
I'm the one
controlling the game.
[KANON]
That's right, Suzaku.
If you had only informed Prince
Schneizel from the very start,
we could have
avoided this battle.
Being that you're one
of the Knights of the Round,
you won't be subjected
to disciplinary action.
However, you'll have to answer
to the sins of your own heart.
[SUZAKU]
What should I do?
[KANON]
Be realistic.
The world won't become
a kinder place only for you.
[SUZAKU]
Do I have to pilot it?
The Lancelot armed with
the F.L.E.I.J.A. device?
Will I have to use it...
on Lelouch?
[LELOUCH] How dare you
have done this to me!
You who sneered at me,
trampled me, looked down on me!
I swear to you, I'll win!
I have to win against
Schneizel and Suzaku!
I realize now that
I'm the one you're after.
I'm the target.
Very well! Have at me, then!
Take your best shot!
I'll destroy you!
I'll show you despair!
And to top it off,
I'll steal Nunnally back!
I'll rescue Kallen!
In the end,
I'll have the last laugh!