[C.C.]
The young Britannian, Lelouch,
is faced with a choice
between two divergent paths.
One leads to the past in a quest
to find his mother's enemies.
The other way
takes him to the future
where he will
create a world in which
his little sister, Nunnally,
can live happily.
Only Lelouch can choose
which direction he will go...
Will he follow
the path that ends
in destruction of the world?
Or will he travel the road
to building a bright new one?
[INOUE] We used to
have trouble getting
even a single motorcycle.
Now we have a submarine.
The military district
of India will be in big trouble
if the Britannians
ever find out.
How'd she do it?
[ZERO] Now then, due to
our recent reorganization,
a few changes have been made.
Our new Chief
of Military Affairs
will be Kyoshiro Tohdoh.
[BLACK KNIGHTS exclaiming]
[ZERO] Taking charge of
all intelligence, espionage,
and public relation matters,
Diethard Reid.
[BLACK KNIGHTS groaning]
This Britannian pretty boy?
Not to mention
his media ties.
Zero, I'm not a racist,
but what's your reasoning
for placing one of "them"
in such a sensitive position?
[ZERO]
Reasoning?
And what of me, I ask you?
[ZERO]
I'm not Japanese either.
You all know this.
What matters is the
ability to produce results.
Who you are and where you're
from are of little consequence.
All right, all right already...
[ZERO] My deputy commander
will be Kaname Oghi.
Who, me?
[ZERO]
You object?
Uh, no...
Well, you were our
leader to begin with,
weren't you?
A newbie can't
take that job, right?
[ZERO] And for research
and development, Rakshata.
Who else?
[ZERO] Captain of the Zero
Squad, Kallen Kouzuki.
[KALLEN]
The Zero Squad?
[ZERO] An elite guard
under my direct command.
Think of yourselves
as my personal force.
[KALLEN]
An elite guard...
Zero...
[ZERO] Captain of the First
Squad will be Shougo Asahina.
Second Squad, Ryouga Senba.
Third Squad, Kizuna Kagesaki.
[ZERO] And Tamaki will lead
the second special forces.
That is all.
[TAMAKI]
I'm the man!
There's no position for C.C.?
[DIETHARD]
Zero. May I add something?
[ZERO]
Hm?
There's one issue that
still needs to be dealt with.
[NOBLEMAN A] Who cares if
he's an honorary Britannian?
Knighting an Eleven is just...
[NOBLEWOMAN A]
And broadcasting it live...
[NOBLEMAN B] How'd he ever
win her favor, I wonder?
[NOBLEMAN A] Well, even
a princess has needs, right?
[NOBLES laughing]
Are they kidding?!
No, this can't be happening!
They're making him a major!
An Eleven!
[EUPHEMIA]
Suzaku Kururugi.
Wilt thou, upon this day,
pledge thy fealty to Britannia
and stand as a
Knight of the Crown?
Yes, Your Highness.
[EUPHEMIA] Dost thou wish
to abandon thy self
and be sword and shield for
the sake of the greater good?
[SUZAKU]
Yes, Your Highness.
I, Euphemia li Britannia,
do hearby dub thee
Sir Suzaku Kururugi.
[TECH] So whose payroll
is he on now?
[CECILE] I believe Lloyd's
already working on that.
[TECH]
You mean... with him?
Yes, well, it's not like
I've ever met him, of course.
[applause]
[DIETHARD]
Suzaku Kururugi.
He's become a focal point
among Elevens
who are Britannian supporters.
I recommend he be assassinated.
[ZERO]
Assassinate him?
He may be right.
You've been the focus
of the resistance movement.
The servile masses
lack such a hero.
[DIETHARD] People aren't
moved by ideology alone.
But the Brittanians will hold
this boy up as a symbol.
I think that taking him out
would be the smart
decision right now.
[TOHDOH]
I object.
[DIETHARD]
Hm?
[TOHDOH] The Japanese would be
revolted by such a cowardly act.
Yeah!
And the Black Knights
are not in the business
of killing the
defenseless, either!
What do you want us to do?!
Get him when he's alone,
and kill him straight out?!
Calm down.
I'm merely suggesting
we minimize a risk
in the most efficient
way possible.
But it's Zero's call, of course.
[C.C.]
What's so complicated?
Just use your Geass on Kururugi.
Drop it.
So stubborn...
Why not?
Because he's your friend?
Or is it pride?
[LELOUCH gasps]
All of it.
[C.C.] You might have
to kill him, otherwise...
[EUPHEMIA] You haven't said
anything about it yet.
[CORNELIA] Appointing a knight
is a privilege of royalty.
It's out of my hands,
even as viceroy.
Don't you see? Suzaku Kururugi
is an honorary Britannian,
and he's proved himself more
than worthy of knighthood.
Sister, even you have to--
It's Viceroy.
Viceroy, even you must
know that he's deserving.
[CORNELIA] Discrimination
against the Numbers
is our national policy!
Then it's time I
tried to change that!
Oh is it now, Sub Viceroy?
Well, when you become Empress,
feel free to do so.
[EMPEROR] Construction
of the thought elevator
is proceeding as scheduled.
[EMPEROR]
Yes... I understand.
What, Schneizel?
[RETAINER]
Yes, Majesty. Your orders?
You needn't interfere.
If he's that sure of himself,
let him challenge me.
Okay guys, time to raise
a glass to Kururugi here,
valued member of the student
council and knight of the realm!
Now let's get this
party started, huh?!
[STUDENTS]
Congratulations!
[STUDENTS cheering]
You've Nunnally
to thank for all of this.
I'm sure you've tired
of the celebrations.
If you don't mind,
we want to honor you too.
Not at all.
It's really kind of you.
Oh... What am I going to do...
Princess Euphemia...
[LLOYD]
Good afternoon!
Have you seen Major Kururugi?
They said I could find him here.
Ooh, looks like you're
working on some fun stuff!
[NINA]
You know what it is?
[LLOYD] Oh, I can tell a
uranium isotope when I see one.
Wow, you know your stuff!
And if you can get that uranium
to absorb active neutrons,
then it should split
into high speed neutrons,
and atomic nuclei!
The problem is,
you'd need to fuel
the reaction with U-235,
which only makes up 0.7%
of all natural uranium.
So even if we came up with
some means of inducing fission,
we'd never have
enough raw materials.
That's why...
Hey Prez, where's Nina?
I told her to be here.
Oh. Hey, Kallen!
Can you help me
set out more pizza?
Hey, are you listening?
[KALLEN]
This is for Zero, Kallen.
If you don't do it here...
[gasps]
Hey!
I think Shirley wants
you to give her a hand.
I'm sorry, but I'm right
in the middle of something
at the moment.
What're you doing?
Maybe I can help out.
[SUZAKU]
Hey.
I'm sorry, I got held up.
Huh?
[SUZAKU]
No problem!
I'm just happy
you could be here.
Hey, what did
you wanna talk about?
You said it was kind
of important, right?
Oh... yeah, uh...
Just forget it.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[LLOYD]
Bad news, Suzaku!
You just got even more
work to do, I'm afraid.
Oh, right...
You know him?
He's my boss.
[MILLY]
Lloyd, is something wrong?
Oh...
Do you guys know each other?
We're to be married.
[NINA]
Huh?!
[STUDENTS]
Isn't that right, honey bunch?
Uh... Yeah...
Secret's out.
So you knew?
Mhm.
Whoa! Whoa!
What's goin' on here?!
Who is this guy?
[MILLY]
Earl Asplund.
Earl?!
It's an honor,
Your Lordship.
Now, what did you say your
relationship was again?
She and I are betrothed.
No!
You were serious then?
So do I have
military duties, then?
Yes.
An important someone-or-other
is arriving by boat.
We're off to meet him.
Along with the Lancelot,
and Princess Euphemia,
naturally.
[STUDENTS gasping, squealing]
[SUZAKU]
Why Shikine Island?
The Tokyo Settlement
would've been a lot safer.
[CECILE] Yes, I'm curious
about that myself.
[SUZAKU]
Wha--?!
You're saying you
don't know either?
Ditto.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?!
You still shouldn't
have said anything.
After all, your loose lips got
our plans leaked onto the net.
That girl was so charming
though, I couldn't resist.
[ZERO]
Euphemia is going to that island
to meet a noble
from their homeland.
Her knight, Suzaku Kururugi,
will be accompanying her.
That far out at sea, the enemy's
strength will be limited.
It is a golden opportunity.
Our objective is
the capture of the Lancelot
and Suzaku Kururugi.
Once we've won the battle,
I want Kururugi
taken safely into custody.
[TOHDOH sighs]
[TAMAKI] So what happens
after we've got him?
[ZERO] Don't worry.
Just leave that to me.
[RAKSHATA]
That's our spot, huh?
You suppose it's going to work?
I think we'll be fine.
The stealth effect we get as a
byproduct seems to be working.
How can you tell?
The Britannians haven't
found us, have they?
What's that tell you?
Oh, I see. You're right!
[RAKSHATA] It is just
a first step, though.
[ZERO] Diethard, what did
you talk Kallen into doing?
I told her to dig up
what she could on Kururugi.
Maybe I implied a
little more than that...
[ZERO]
Don't overstep your bounds.
I don't recall ordering
his assassination.
You want us to be the
hammer of justice, right?
We can't have
people thinking of us
as cold-blooded killers, I know.
But we can hide the
truth using the media.
You can't change the world
without getting
your hands dirty.
Am I wrong?
[ZERO]
Diethard...
What are you really after?
You may have been demoted,
but you're still a Britannian.
You don't need to
join the Black Knights
to change the world, do you?
I never mentioned this,
but the first time
I ever saw you
was the night
you rescued Kururugi.
And I trembled!
It was like a new era had taken
form and appeared before me!
I wish to document you, Zero,
as you build your organization
and topple over the empire,
then take this world
for your own.
I wish to be there documenting
history as it's created!
Nothing has ever made
my heart dance more!
[ZERO]
Documenting?
You're right in the thick of it.
I'd say you're
fabricating history.
Objectivity is a fairy tale.
In the end, journalism is
a product of the human mind,
like everything else.
[ZERO] You're not to
interfere with military matters.
[DIETHARD]
Yes, of course.
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT] Arrival
time's right on schedule.
We've prepared a room
for you back at headquarters,
if you'd care to wait there.
Is it safe to assume
that the ship is docking here?
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT]
Yes, that hasn't changed.
This will do fine, then.
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT] Very well,
I'll just arrange for an escort.
Huh?
[FAYER]
Terrorists?!
But how did they get here?!
First Squad,
continue advancing!
Zero Squad, I want you
covering them from their flank!
[BRITANNIAN SOLDIER]
Filthy Elevens!
She sure packs a punch, huh?
[ZERO]
Impressive.
It's no wonder Tohdoh held off
the Britannians once before
without a single Knightmare.
Now I only have
to wait for Euphemia
to receive word of our visit...
Headquarters appears to be
under some sort of attack!
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
We'll withdraw
to the settlement.
Can you arrange
an escort unit for her?
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT] It's too
risky to leave right now.
They're jamming us with some
kind of wide-range interference.
You're going to be fine.
Don't worry, Princess, I won't
let any harm come to you.
No, Suzaku,
you should help these men
fend off the attack.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
But Sub-Viceroy,
he's an Honorary Britannian!
We're almost certainly dealing
with the Black Knights here.
What if he turns the
Lancelot against us?
Uh, you do realize
you're criticizing
a member of royalty, right?
Oh, uh, forgive me,
I didn't mean to...
Kururugi.
Demonstrate your valor
for us today
so that we may finally
silence all these nay-sayers.
Right!
Worthless garrison unit!
I'll finish the job!
Huh?!
[groans]
Zero... There you are...
[ZERO]
That's right, Suzaku. Come!
Confirming target.
All units assume
formation three and fall back!
Do not fire on the target!
I repeat, do not fire!
[FAYER] Yes,
thanks to the Special Corps.
What?!
But that would mean...
Yes, Your Highness!
[SUZAKU] He's not equipped for
that sand he jumped into...
Could he be drawing me
into a set up,
using himself as bait?
Fine then!
Zero! I got you...
[ZERO]
...right where...
...I want you.
What the...?!
It's frozen?
No good!
[ZERO]
We need to talk, Kururugi.
I suggest you come out.
Your secondary systems should
still be functioning.
You'll be treated as a prisoner
under international law.
Of course,
if you don't care to talk,
we could just gun you down.
I don't care!
Tell Suzaku to abandon the unit!
What could possibly
be wrong with it?
How come it won't move?
Something's happened
to the Sakuradite
that's powering
Suzaku's Lancelot.
Somebody is interfering with it!
[LLOYD]
A Gefjun Disturber.
You mean...
But they're actually
using it as a jamming mechanism.
I thought it only theoretical.
What a fool I am.
It really is you, Rakshata.
It's looks like
the range and endurance
still need a little work.
[ZERO] I'll get straight to
the point, Suzaku Kururugi.
I want you to join me.
[SUZAKU]
Is that a threat?
Well you can forget it.
I already told you.
Results gained through
contemptable means
are worthless to me.
[ZERO] So you wouldn't
describe the peace we have now
as worthless?
[SUZAKU gasps]
[ZERO] If Japan had resisted
to its very last breath
seven years ago,
what do you think
would have happened?
The Chinese and the E.U.
would have stepped in,
and split Japan in three.
They'd be fighting even now.
Our current peace is the result
of Japan's immediate and
unconditional surrender.
That's right.
And I've been fighting to
preserve my father's peace,
ever since it began!
[ZERO]
You're wrong.
Prime Minister Kururugi,
elected by the people,
didn't choose surrender.
That decision was selfishly
made by his killer.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[ZERO] With the government
thrown into chaos,
surrender became
the only logical choice.
The will of the people
was stolen from them
by a lone criminal pursuing
his own selfish agenda!
Can you hear them at all?
[CECILE] There's too much
static on the mic!
H-How on earth
do you know that?
[ZERO] There's only
one way for you to atone now.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[ZERO]
Present the Japanese people
with the choice they
weren't able to make then.
The path they were robbed
of seven years ago...
Fighting Britannia.
Fighting them? That again?
[ZERO] It's an option
worth exploring.
Or would you rather
drive the masses
towards a future dictated
by your own egotism?
You call that peace?
[radio static]
[FAYER]
...Major Kururugi?
Please respond!
May I?
[ZERO]
As you wish.
[FAYER]
This is Lt. Col. Fayer,
commander here
on Shikine Island!
We're launching
surface to surface missiles
against the terrorists!
Major Kururugi, your
orders are to keep Zero there!
[ZERO]
They're giving him up to die!
Kururugi, what're you...?!
[SUZAKU] I can't approve
of your methods!
All I can do right now is this!
Why you little--!
[TOHDOH] Don't move!
The field'll affect you too!
But Zero!
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT]
We're assigning Portman here
to escort them.
The Sub-Viceroy should be--
[EUPHEMIA]
Wait!
[LLOYD] You're going
to destroy the Lancelot?!
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT]
Kururugi is holding Zero there.
This is our chance to kill him!
And whose idea was this?
Major Kururugi's
my personal knight!
It was a para-level one order.
It can only be countermanded
by the consensus
of at least
three ranking generals
or the Viceroy herself,
I'm afraid.
Then who exactly
issued this order, Captain?
Get me a line
to them immediately!
Para-level one order,
Princess Euphemia.
[EUPHEMIA]
Out of my way!
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT]
Sub-Viceroy!
Contact the base!
Tell them there's a chance
I'll be caught in the attack!
See if they'll initiate
their launch then!
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT]
Please stop this!
Think what you're doing!
But they'll stop with
the princess out there...
I'm not sure
they will, unfortunately.
[CHIBA]
Incoming missiles confirmed!
Damn!
Hold on! I'm coming!
Dammit!
[ZERO]
You're gonna die here as well!
You don't have a
problem with that?!
[FAYER] Your sacrifice
isn't in vain, Major!
We're about to put an end
to the most dangerous criminal
our homeland has ever known.
They'll speak of your
bravery for generations to come!
[ZERO]
Shut up!
All Knightmares,
target on those missiles
and throw up a barrage!
Empty your guns if you have to!
[KALLEN]
Suzaku, let Zero go!
It's me... Suzaku!
It's Kallen Stadtfeld,
from the student council!
Look at me!
[EUPHEMIA]
Suzaku... You can't die now!
[SUZAKU] A soldier must
always follow his orders!
[ZERO] Certainly easier
than following your own heart!
How do you feel about this?!
[SUZAKU]
You're wrong!
I have rules that I made
and need to live by!
[KALLEN gasps]
They completed a float system?
Well I'm not done...
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
[EUPHEMIA]
That's... my brother's Avalon!
No, it can't be!
[ZERO] Damn it, Suzaku! Do
something! You're going to die!
[SUZAKU] Better that
than breaking the rules!
[ZERO]
You stubborn fool!
[LELOUCH] My Geass is
the power to command others.
None can disobey...
Those I turn it on
find their ethics, their
thoughts, and their feelings
crushed beneath its power.
And knowing all of that,
I use it... on Suzaku.