[SWIM CLUB A]
So? Tell us!
How are things with
you and Lelouch?
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
[SWIM CLUB B] You two are the
official school couple now,
aren't you?
[SWIM CLUB C]
Have you kissed yet?
Um, th-that was
just for the event.
We're not fooling around.
[VILLETTA]
Don't be embarrassed.
It's no secret that
you've always
had a big crush on Lelouch.
Oh! Not you too,
Coach Villetta!
[VILLETTA]
But you love him, don't you?
Enough to shoot me?
Huh?
[VILLETTA] It's been very
difficult, you know?
Having to come here and spend
each day cheerfully smiling
at the young woman who shot me.
My true feelings
have to be hidden
behind the mask of a teacher.
[gasps]
[VILLETTA] Shirley Fenette...
How dare you!
How dare you shoot me!
[whimpering]
[footsteps]
Lulu!
Uh?
[SHIRLEY screams]
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[SHIRLEY] That's right.
While Lelouch was Zero,
he killed my father.
[LELOUCH]
So, Jianmen pass has fallen?
We've also taken over the air
force facility in Macau.
We should send
Asahina and Hong Gu
to defend Jianmenguan.
And why don't we assign
Minase and Sugiyama
to take charge of
municipal affairs there?
[ROLO] Well, looks like
things are going smoothly.
[LELOUCH] Our so-called foes
are just local military factions
that won't join us,
but they'll deploy forces
without talking to each other.
Not to mention that you've
already got a hold of
the empress. The one leader who
could unify all those factions.
[LELOUCH]
Exactly.
You're off?
I'm going to Ikebukuro.
But I'll help you with the
rest of your homework
when I return.
I'll catch you later, then.
[bell tolls]
[ARTHUR yawns]
[SHIRLEY] Lulu was Zero. And
coach Villetta was a soldier.
And Kallen was one of
the Black Knights.
Then what about Nina?
And the Prez? And Rivalz?
Is our school the weirdest
place on Earth?
Oh, why is Nunnally
now the viceroy?
What are the lies,
and what is the truth?
[ANNOUNCER] Attention: The local
express is running 10 minutes
behind schedule and will be
arriving at platform three.
For those passengers who
do not wish to wait...
[LELOUCH]
Very well.
For the first stage,
this will be fine.
[MAN A]
All right then,
we'll continue with
the same procedure.
[MALL ANNOUNCER] And now, here's
an announcement to all our
patrons about a special deal.
For a limited time only,
we're running a campaign...
[SUZAKU]
Shirley!
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Wait! It's just me.
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
So what's wrong? Why'd you
want to me to come here?
[SHIRLEY]
Um...
Uh...
[LELOUCH]
Shirley!
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch.
[VILLETTA]
Where's Lelouch? On a date?
At the moment, he's out
testing the G cars.
[VILLETTA]
Hmpf. How convenient.
[ROLO]
Huh?
Rolo, why have you
turned your back
on your country? Unlike me,
you were dispatched here by
the Order, so why would you--
Just why are you
asking me that?
What's between my
brother and me is--
--[alarm sounds]
--[BOTH] Uh!
[FEMALE COMM]
B7 to control.
Suspicious male sighted
near the chapel.
B5 and B9 have moved
in to apprehend him.
[TEACHERS gasps]
[JEREMIAH]
Hmpf.
Look what happened simply
by asking where Lelouch was.
Lord Jeremiah! But how?!
[FEMALE COMM] Target is
moving toward the clubhouse.
B2 and B8 have been
eliminated, as well.
Sound a school-wide alarm!
Get students out of the
vicinity of the target!
[TEACHER gasping]
[FEMALE COMM] Attention all
students and personnel.
This is an emergency
announcement.
Do not go near
the clubhouse area.
A suspicious person
has been sighted there.
[JEREMIAH]
Out of my way.
I have no desire to kill
a woman if I don't need to.
[SAYOKO]
We at least share that.
I, too, would like to avoid
any unnecessary killing.
Oh?
[SAYOKO]
En garde!
Cyborg?!
And I have Zero to thank.
[BARTLEY] They say
they're going to kill God.
[CORNELIA]
God?
I thought they were speaking
metaphorically, but now...
At the very least these people
believe what they're saying!
Ridiculous. To believe in God.
There's no such being!
[V.V.]
That's right.
[BARTLEY, CORNELIA gasp]
[V.V.] No winged goddesses
or long-bearded old men
in white gowns with
kingdoms in the clouds.
No. Not that sort of God. Uh!
[BARTLEY]
Uh!
[CORNELIA]
Hmpf.
[gasps] Princess Cornelia!
Who knows what type
of Geass he controls!
You must never let your
guard down, even for a child.
[V.V.]
Yes, that's correct.
Cornelia, you do live up to
your reputation, don't you?
As your uncle, I'm
very proud of you.
My what?!
[V.V.]
We made a solemn vow.
If there was ever a god that
made men fight each other...
...we'd kill him
and his divine rule.
[SAYOKO]
Even if you are a cyborg,
your exposed human parts
make you vulnerable!
[JEREMIAH]
You have good aim!
[SAYOKO] I'll stop you!
For Master Lelouch's sake!
[JEREMIAH]
Uh?!
[JEREMIAH] Your skill in
martial arts is impressive.
But, it won't impede
Jeremiah Gottwald.
[SAYOKO grunts]
[ROLO]
Sayoko!
[SAYOKO]
Uh!
[JEREMIAH]
Dammit.
Steal time!
[ROLO] Okay! Now get him while
I'm holding him still! Go on!
With great pleasure!
[gasps, screams]
But that's not possible!
My Geass...
It should stop time
with absolutely anyone!
[JEREMIAH]
Rolo Lamperouge!
[ROLO grunts]
[JEREMIAH] Just as I thought!
You've been fooled!
[ROLO] But how could
you break my Geass?
[JEREMIAH] How? Because I
was chosen, that's how!
Picked by the Order
to be an assassin!
[ROLO] Then you've come to
kill Lelouch, is that it?!
[VILLETTA]
Lord Jeremiah!
--[JEREMIAH] Huh?
--[ROLO] Uh?
[JEREMIAH] Villetta! You mean
Lelouch has snared you, too?!
Lelouch is at the Ikebukuro
station right now!
[JEREMIAH gasps]
Lord Jeremiah, I'm begging you!
What ever you do,
please let me go!
[ROLO grunts]
[JEREMIAH]
All right, then.
[SHIRLEY] What do I do?
I called Suzaku out here,
but what should I say to him?
Especially with Lulu here.
[LELOUCH] Shirley, what kind
of game are you playing?
Or was it Suzaku who
called her out here?
[SUZAKU]
Rivalz told me
that Lelouch has been here
in Japan the entire time.
Intelligence from the O.S.I.
backs that up, also.
But... Why don't I believe it?
Villetta. What are you doing?
Are you betraying
Lelouch, or... are you--
We should contact
Lelouch right away.
I will stay here and
protect the place.
The rest of you go
on to Ikebukuro.
If Lelouch is ready for him,
we may be able to pin
Jeremiah from two sides.
[SHIRLEY] I have to tell
Suzaku. He needs to know
that Lelouch is Zero and
the he killed my father!
This is the boundary
line, right here.
[SUZAKU] The demarcation between
the settlement and the ghettos.
We have to erase it.
[SHIRLEY gasps] Hold it. What
if these two are accomplices?
To turn Area 11
back into Japan?
That's it! They've been
friends since way back!
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[LELOUCH, SUZAKU]
Uh?
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
[SHIRLEY]
No!
Shirley!
[SHIRLEY]
Stay away from me!
[LELOUCH]
Shirley!
You're both liars! You two are
nothing but a pair of fakes!
I won't... Aaggh...!
[LELOUCH grunts]
[gasps]
[LELOUCH grunting]
[SHIRLEY gasps]
No! Let me go! Let me go!
Stop it! I can't lose you!
[SHIRLEY gasps]
I don't want to lose you
or anyone else in my life!
Not one more person!
Please...
Shirley!
Uh-huh.
Uh! Suzaku!
[SHIRLEY] Hey... You've done
this once before, haven't you?
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[SHIRLEY] You know,
that time back at school
when you tried to catch Arthur.
Yeah, you're right.
[LELOUCH]
Uh?
I guess you're right Shirley.
We have done this before.
And Suzaku is always the
one who pulls you back up.
If Lelouch had been
the one on top,
both of us would have fallen.
[LELOUCH]
You exercise nut!
If you're gonna brag,
you should've saved
us before we fell.
That's ridiculous.
[SUZAKU]
Why am I laughing?
After what Lelouch
did to Euphy!
[SHIRLEY] I'm wrong.
He's alone. Lulu is...
[ringing]
[LELOUCH]
Oh.
'Scuse me. Uh?!
[ROLO]
Lelouch, be careful!
Jeremiah's heading
toward you right now!
He's an assassin
sent by the Order.
My Geass didn't work on him!
Wait, Jeremiah is alive?!
And what do you mean
an assassin, Rolo?
[ROLO]
I'm not sure.
Anyway, don't do anything
rash until we get there.
What's up?
Is something wrong?
[LELOUCH] This is bad.
With Suzaku here...
By your expression,
I'm guessing that wasn't
a friendly phone call.
Ah, ow!
Suzaku, stop that!
My problem comes
first, doesn't it?
Right.
[LELOUCH]
Oh, yeah, that's right,
you two were waiting for
each other here, weren't you?
What's the matter,
are you jealous?
[LELOUCH]
Hmpf.
Thanks so much, Lulu.
Can't we wait for just
a while? We should--
[SHIRLEY]
Come on. Let's go, Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
Wait! Hold on!
[LELOUCH] This area is about to
become a battlefield. And I
can think of no safer place for
Shirley, than to be with Suzaku.
[POLICEMAN A]
Jeremiah Gottwald?
Yes, I am.
[BOTH]
What?
The guy's bulletproof!
I understand. Lelouch has
used his Geass on you.
Huh?
Huh?!
[POLICEMEN grunting]
[LELOUCH] Not only does
Geass have no effect on him,
he has the power to
cancel it, as well.
[MAN A]
Fire?!
[MAN B]
Terrorists?!
[JEREMIAH]
Hmph.
[LELOUCH] Right! Come up
and get me, Orange!
[SUZAKU] So, what's
this important thing
you need to talk to me about?
Uh, well I'm...
Well, I'm in love with Lulu.
[SHIRLEY]
But you hate him, don't you?
[SUZAKU]
I liked him...
...at one time.
[SHIRLEY]
And now?
[SUZAKU sighs]
[SHIRLEY] I thought
something was wrong.
The two of you used to
be so close together.
What happened,
did you have a fight?
I can't forgive him.
Nothing is unforgivable,
you know.
In other words,
it only means that you're
not willing to forgive him.
You don't want
to forgive him.
[gasps]
I forgave him. I chose
to a long time ago.
Shirley... What are you...
--[explosion]
--[SHOPPERS scream]
[POLICEMAN C] Did you call
the fire department?
In situations like
this, doesn't the
Army respond first?
[POLICEMEN gasp]
Sir Suzaku Kururugi!
I'm the Knight of Seven.
Uh! M-My lord!
This might be an act of
terrorism, so from here on,
I'm taking command
of all the perimeter police
and fire fighting units.
[BOTH]
Right, understood, my lord!
And I want you to protect
that young woman
right over there.
[OHGI] What is it? We're in
the middle of a meeting.
[TAMAKI] Like I care? Ain't
no meeting I was invited to!
Emergency call from Zero.
Somethin' weird's
going on there.
[OHGI]
Uh?
Zero! It's Ohgi.
[gasps]
[OHGI] What's happened?
What's the emergency?
If it's about the guys from
Taiwan, right now we're--
Ohgi!
[OHGI]
Mm! That voice! It's--
[sirens]
Lelouch, just hang in there!
All units in position.
Support teams en route.
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu...
[POLICEMAN F] Please get
into the vehicle, Miss.
It's the Knight of
Seven's orders.
Wha...?! Miss, come back here!
Hold on, Lulu!
Don't worry, I won't
leave you alone!
[JEREMIAH]
You won't escape me!
Lulu, where can you be? Uh!
[SHIRLEY]
He must be fighting.
Lulu's fighting...
...on his own.
A mechanical body...
And you've got a
Geass canceller.
Your vengefulness is truly
top-notch, Orange boy!
There's no vengefulness.
It's sheer loyalty.
How I hate to hear that.
What could the emperor
have possibly done
to deserve such loyalty?
Wha...?!
From your performance,
I figured that you must
be using sakuradite.
[JEREMIAH]
A Gefijun Disturber...!
[LELOUCH] Well, well, I see
you've done your homework.
You're aware, that when
this sakuradite disruption
system is complete,
we can paralyze all
urban functions
with the railway's
circular route.
In other words, bring
Tokyo to a standstill.
I'm grateful. You've been
an exemplary test subject.
[ROLO panting]
Rolo!
Shirley, you're here?!
[SHIRLEY]
Answer me, Rolo.
Um.
Do you truly... love Lulu?
[LELOUCH]
Now then,
are you going to tell me
what I want to know?
Where is the Order located?
And where is V.V.?
You're the one...
who will talk here!
What?!
Because I have...
my reasons...
I'm resolved to see
my loyalty through!
I must know the truth for
certain... once and for all!
But how...?!
He shouldn't be able to move!
Why, Lelouch? Why did you
adopt the role of Zero?
Why did you turn
against your homeland?
Becoming an enemy of
the emperor as a result?!
I did it because I am
Lelouch vi Britannia!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] My father,
the Britannian emperor,
allowed my mother to be killed!
In so doing, he stole
Nunnally's sight...
her legs... and our
futures from us!
[LELOUCH yells]
[JEREMIAH] I know. I remember,
because I was there, too.
Uh?! You were?!
My first assignment.
To guard her. Lady Marianne,
whom I loved and respected.
But I failed to carry
through with that loyalty.
I just wasn't able
to protect her!
So you founded the
Purebloods, then?
Master Lelouch.
Everything is
becoming clear now.
You became Zero for the
sake of Lady Marianne,
didn't you?
But if you didn't
come here to kill me,
then what are you trying to do?
I don't serve V.V...
I follow only one.
It's Lady Marianne...
Now... I'll die without regret.
Lord Jeremiah!
[JEREMIAH gasping]
[JEREMIAH]
Ugh! My prince...!
Jeremiah Gottwald, listen.
Your steadfast loyalty
is still desperately needed
here. Isn't that right?
[JEREMIAH gasping]
Indeed. Yes, Your Majesty.
[SHIRLEY] Rolo, I love Lulu.
But what about you?
What a question.
He's my only brother,
so of course I love him.
Then you're on Lulu's
side, right? Right?!
Uh?
Please. Let me join you!
I want Lulu to be safe, too!
I can help you protect him!
[ROLO exhales]
I want to bring all the
happiness back into Lulu's life!
Then maybe he can be together
with his sister Nunna!
[ROLO gasps]
[LELOUCH] Right. I've sent
Jeremiah on ahead.
He'll take care of any
obstacles in the way.
Don't try to fight him!
He just came over to our side!
Uh?
[gasps]
Shirley!
Shirley, who did this to you?!
Lulu...?
I'm glad... we can talk
at the very end...
[LELOUCH] Don't say that!
It's not the end!
I'll call a doctor, so just--
Ever since my memories
have come back,
I've been feeling
so very afraid...
[LELOUCH gasps]
[SHIRLEY]
A teacher who wasn't a teacher.
Friends who don't...
have memories to share.
Everyone... was just... lying...
It felt as though... the whole
world was spying on me.
That's the world...
you've been fighting...
all by yourself, isn't it?
All alone...
So that's why I...
why I wanted
to be someone who would at
least be truthful to you.
Shirley...
Lulu... I love you.
Even knowing how you caught
my father in all this...
I simply couldn't hate you.
[LELOUCH whimpers]
[SHIRLEY] Even though you
made me forget everything...
I still fell in love with you...
Even though my memories
were tampered with...
I kept falling in love...
...with you all over again...
No, Shirley! You can't die...!
[SHIRLEY] No matter how
many times I'm reborn...
I'll keep falling in love...
with you, Lulu...
I suppose... that
it's simply fate...
No, don't die!
I order you not to die...!
[SHIRLEY] So, is that
okay then... Lulu...?
And as I'm reborn...
I'll fall in love with
you over and over...
I'll keep...
...falling...
...in love... with...
[LELOUCH gasps]
Shirley! Shirley...!
[LELOUCH yells]
[LELOUCH]
C.C. once told me something.
She said that Geass was
the power of the king.
And a life of solitude.
Then this must be
what she meant.
Shirley... I wanted...
I had to apologize for
involving you with Geass.
For making you the sacrifice.
How can I make up for that?
Tell me, please. Tell me...