[JEREMIAH]
Code R... I see.
You've given me an abnormally
high active electric potential
and boosted my neurofilaments.
Oh, how understanding
is such a happiness.
You want me experimented
in order to recreate
it, didn't you?
This affliction of hers.
Stop it! Code R
is not an invalid!
Regardless, won't you
just please calm down?!
Your brain cells were destroyed
past the Circle of
Willis arteries, so--
[JEREMIAH]
Spare me excuses!
You're the one who
gave me like this
because you hated me for sending
you back to the Homeland!
Look, I promise I'll hear
anything you have to say,
but first, let's return
to the Homeland!
We can't carry on a proper
conversation in this situation!
[ZERO]
Hear me, Britannia!
--This is Zero!
--Zero?
[ZERO]
A rebel against oppressors
who abuse their power!
We will wait until midnight!
You have till then
to surrender to me!
Through the entire settlement?!
[RESEARCHER A] He's on
every communication channel.
Do we have any communication
to the outside?
[CORNELIA]
Use this opportunity to confirm
the enemy's formation.
[SOLDIER]
Yes, Your Highness.
I'll have vengeance for
my sister Euphemia,
and I'll take it right
here and now, Zero!
Fairly, out in the open,
and face-to-face.
A rebel against oppressors
who abuse their power.
We will wait until midnight!
You have till then
to surrender to me!
Surrender at midnight!
Hand over the whole
settlement to them...
Hey! Wh-What are you doing?!
Stop it!
You know what'll happen
if you do that?!
[OPERATOR A]
Would you please not interfere?
This is no time to
be screwing around!
--If you don't stop it--
--[gunshot]
[CORNELIA] Are you ready
to commence the air raid?
[SOLDIER]
Strike is synchronized.
[CORNELIA]
Good.
Assume the position to fire!
Cornelia, I'm afraid
a direct confrontation
with me in battle
will be your undoing.
[CORNELIA]
What?!
--[RIVALZ gasps]
--An earthquake?!
[MILLY, NUNNALLY gasp]
[ZERO]
A layered structure,
built to be
earthquake resistant.
But if you demolish all of the
floor sections simultaneously,
you won't find anything
to be more fragile.
By lining up at the
city's perimeter
to engage the Black Knights,
you sealed your fate!
I'm not beaten yet!
Damn, you really are
one amazing dude, Zero!
[KAGUYA gasps] Wow! Did they
destroy entire settlement?
I heard only the outer
perimeter was affected.
There are some facilities in it
that we're going to need later.
[DIETHARD] Still... How were
Zero's underground collaborators
able to pull this off?
I'm guessing that Villetta's
and Jeremiah's theories
must have been true.
Heh, then this is magnificent!
Yes... The world is a game,
and people are mere pawns!
[ZERO laughing]
This will do.
Once we broadcast
images to the world
of their government
bureau falling to us,
along with our declaration
of independence,
he'll be forced to face me.
And if I can get him...
Get the Britannian emperor
to meet me one on one,
then all the pieces
will fall into my hands.
[TOHDOH] How does the
enemy's air power look?
Our allied groups
are concentrating
on striking them
hard in each sector.
The rest are around the Izu
areas, Sado, and Awaji islands.
Then the time is right.
Now's our chance!
Attack!
[TOHDOH] Third Squad,
take the media sector!
Sixth Squad, take the harbor!
Special forces,
suppress the lower levels!
All remaining, push
in from the front!
Gather intelligence on the
enemy forces that are left!
[CORNELIA]
All forces, hear me!
Fall back to the Britannian
government bureau!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, Your Highness!
[CORNELIA]
What's wrong?
If you're having
trouble controlling it,
just attach the cockpit block.
No, Princess Cornelia, forget
about me and get to the bureau!
[TOHDOH] Cornelia's been
found! Surround her!
[CORNELIA grunts]
[CORNELIA growls]
Meet your fate!
[CORNELIA]
Tohdoh! You phantom!
[GUILFORD]
No, Princess!
Stand aside! Leave him to me!
[CORNELIA gasps]
Guilford!
Well, it's the one from Narita!
Get away while
you can, Princess!
Do you expect me to simply
abandon my men and run away?!
[GUILFORD] Your Highness,
you must survive!
For Princess Euphemia's
honor, as well!
[CORNELIA gasps]
[GUILFORD]
Go now!
Because, m'lady, I am the knight
you chose to champion you!
That sword's the same
one as the Lancelot's!
[GUILFORD] Therefore, I must be
the one who stays and fights!
So be it.
Then, Guilford, your orders are
to come back alive, my knight.
Yes, Your Highness,
I will return.
[ZERO]
The school area is a priority
for the special force and
the Zero Squad to take over.
We'll use one of the buildings
for a command center.
What? At the school?
[ZERO] Ohgi, you stand
by out there, as well.
Ohgi!
Uh... Right. Understood, Zero.
--[phone rings]
--[footsteps]
[LLOYD]
You're planning to go
to the Tokyo settlement,
aren't you?
However... You can't have it!
The A.S.E.E.C. exists for
research and development.
It appears our duties here
have wound to an end.
And we haven't been
ordered by the viceroy
to go out there, either.
Leaving would be a
violation of orders, right?
[CECILE] Suzaku, I know
how you feel, but...
Oh, no you don't!
[LLOYD groans]
--[CECILE gasps]
--[LLOYD grunts]
Listen to me.
Zero's in Tokyo,
and I'm gonna finish
him with my own hands!
I won't let you stop me!
I'm doing this!
[ASAHINA]
Colonel!
[SENBA] Lt. Colonel,
should we pursue?
[TOHDOH]
Where are the other units?
They're approaching, climbing
up from the side-- Hm?
[GUILFORD gasps]
The Glaston Knights!
[GLASTON 2]
Lord Guilford,
we're holding a position
just ahead of here.
Please head back.
I appreciate that. I'm grateful.
[GLASTON 3]
Think nothing of it, sir.
Originally, we were
all subordinates
under General Darlton's command.
We still don't know
if he's alive or dead.
But our duty to Viceroy
Cornelia comes first!
[GUILFORD]
Do you know the situation?
The enemy's frontal
assault is a diversion.
But if we beat them here, the
rest are simply militia forces.
I mean... They're just rabble.
Diethard! Enemy air
power's been taken care of!
Kaguya will command the G1.
Move to your assigned
location immediately!
[DIETHARD]
Understood.
Yoshida, get the Raikou ready!
[YOSHIDA]
Yes, sir!
Tamaki, do you know
Rakshata's status?
[TAMAKI]
She's on the move!
Kallen, go provide her
group with back-up!
[KALLEN]
Right!
Tohdoh, you know what to
do if you see the target.
[TOHDOH]
Understood.
Okay...
Now, what's the name of
the collaborator, Ohgi?
[OHGI] Uh... I have it
as Sayoko Shinozaki.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[SPEAKER 1] Contact's been lost
with the Hiroshima settlement!
[SPEAKER 2 ]
Uprisings have broken out
in the Sapporo
settlement as well!
[SPEAKER 3] And Chinese
Federation naval fleets
are massing in the
East China Sea!
The Chinese Federation, too?!
That's all we need with His
Majesty still not present!
[SCHNEIZEL]
He must be there again.
Lord Odysseus, our
troops are standing by,
ready for deployment.
You need to choose
a commander, now!
We mustn't be too
hasty here, gentlemen.
What Euphemia did was
clearly an abominable blunder.
Handle this rashly, and it
may spread to every Area.
My lord! We must go to
help Princess Cornelia!
Brother, why don't
I go? Send me there.
Y-You're serious?! Would
you really go there?!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Doesn't it sadden you to see
those people killing each other?
Super electromagnetic
shrapnel cannon, fire!
[MINAMI]
First special forces, move in!
[C.C.]
They only seem to be defending
the government bureau right now.
[LELOUCH] As expected, they're
trying not to scatter themselves
while waiting for
reinforcements.
[SUGIYAMA] Don't move!
We're the Black Knights!
We've taken over this building!
Do exactly as we tell you to!
No...! It can't be!
Hello, Chief. I brought
you an exclusive.
Shall we transmit
this to the world?
The moment when Zero changes
everything in our lives?
Now that's a scoop.
[CHIEF]
R-Right!
We'll give the public
a spectacular show
that'll exceed whatever
they hoped to see!
[RIVALZ]
Huh?
That was it-- the last
broadcasting station.
They're all down!
[ALL gasp]
[TAMAKI]
Hands up and turn around!
The Black Knights
control the school!
All of you are now our hostages!
[RIVALZ grunts]
Lower your guns!
[TAMAKI] Huh? That's a hell of a
thing to say in this situation!
[ARTHUR hisses]
Rivalz!
C'mon, lemme be cool
for once, okay?
I'll protect everyone!
--Is that a fact?
--[MILLY gasps]
--[RIVALZ grunts]
--[ZERO] Stop!
[ALL gasp]
[ZERO] I expressly told
you to avoid violence.
Yeah, but you also told us
this was gonna be our
command center, didn't you?
--Your command center?!
--[RIVALZ] Huh?
[KALLEN] Why does it have to
be Ashford, of all places?!
[ZERO] Your academy
is strategically useful
for our purposes,
therefore, we're turning
it into a command center.
We're in no position
to refuse you.
[ZERO] I guarantee none
of you will be harmed.
[LELOUCH]
Nunnally...
Until the fighting has
ended, you'll be safe here,
protected by the Black Knights.
So please...
[RIVALZ]
Like we can believe you?!
You guys are at war
with us Britannians!
We're enemies, remember?!
[KALLEN]
Please, Rivalz, don't argue.
Do what he says.
--[GROUP gasps]
--[SHIRLEY] Kallen!
Well, well... There's a
surprise around every corner.
Do I have your word
that no one gets hurt?
Not only us, but any of
the student body, faculty,
or staff anywhere on the campus!
[KALLEN] As long as nobody
tries to leave the dorms
or administration offices,
they ought to be fine.
I want-- I want to know
what you did to me!
[KALLEN]
Huh?
I was so terrified!
You have no idea!
Both of you did
something to me.
Tell me the truth! Didn't you?!
[KALLEN]
Huh?
[SHIRLEY]
How could you?! How could you?!
[OHGI]
Zero! It's the Lancelot!
[ZERO]
I knew he'd come!
[SUZAKU]
Out of my way!
[YOSHIDA screams]
When I find you, Zero,
I'm going to kill you!
Geass?
That's correct. Zero possesses
a supernatural power.
[SUZAKU]
Impossible.
Then how do you explain
Princess Euphemia's
sudden and drastic change?
What about you?
The one who always
follows the rules.
How do you account for your
actions on Shikine Island?
In short...
[VILLETTA] The power to control
people and erase their memories!
When you think about it,
it makes sense and explains
everything that's
happened till now.
And as a result of
its aftereffects,
I fell in love with
a damned Eleven!
That student...
Lelouch Lamperouge!
He's responsible for all of it!
[KALLEN]
Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
Kallen?!
[KALLEN]
We meet in battle once again!
I'm sorry, but this time,
you're going to die!
[SUZAKU]
You're all fools!
You, the Japanese,
he's lying to all of you!
I can't put up with that
kind of ignorant drivel!
And what do you even
know about Zero anyway?!
Well, tell me what you
know about him then!
Tell me where Zero is now!
[KALLEN grunts]
Come on! Answer me!
Where's Zero?!
Like I'd tell that to a
filthy traitor like you!
[SUZAKU]
Then let's finish this here!
[KALLEN] Don't think you have
the edge because you can fly!
[SUZAKU grunts]
[KALLEN]
Now I gotcha!
Die!
[KALLEN screams]
[SUZAKU]
Tell me! Where is Zero?!
[KALLEN] You know, I
really hate pushy guys.
Okay... Then die here.
[SUZAKU] If you have any
last words, say them now.
[ZERO]
Wait!
[SUZAKU gasps]
[KALLEN gasps]
[ZERO]
Suzaku Kururugi,
my belief that you and I
could be allies was incorrect.
I'm no longer gullible about
our would-be partnership,
let's resolve this one-on-one.
Works for me! Let's do it!
[ASAHINA]
Colonel?
[TOHDOH]
Asahina. What about Urabe?
He's moving on the energy filler
repository right now, sir.
All right, then let's go
rendezvous with Senba and Chiba.
Once we recharge, we'll
surround the government bureau,
then we, as the main force,
will push in from the front!
[ASAHINA]
Roger!
[CORNELIA]
Order Lord Crane to fall back.
Set up a defense line on
the railway station grounds.
Yes, right away, Your Highness.
[GUILFORD]
Princess Cornelia.
We've completed our formation.
What about a line of
defense around the bureau?
You're to hold your
position, Guilford.
If we can just drag
this battle out,
it'll only go badly
for the Black Knights.
[GUILFORD]
Yes, Your Highness.
[CORNELIA] Well? What did
my older brother say?
He said the Pacific
fleet should arrive
in approximately 75 hours.
Also, the Sado and Tori
Island air divisions
have already been
deployed within Area 11.
[CORNELIA] Meaning that
they should be here
in about 30 minutes.
Leak this information
to the Black Knights!
[GLASTON 1]
Huh?
After that, you'll join Lord
Guilford in the defense line
protecting the
government bureau.
[GLASTON 2]
And you, my lady?
Oh, I'll be preparing the party.
[JEREMIAH]
Zero!
[BARTLEY]
Can't you calm him down?!
I can't his resistance
is too strong!
[RESEARCHER A]
We've mounted the radiator fins!
[DARLTON groans]
[OHGI] T4s headed for
the government bureau?
Are the enemy air
divisions here already?
No, only one unit so far.
[OHGI] Well, it shouldn't
affect too many of us, then.
We're holding the school,
and Diethard's group is
holding the media area.
Miss Kaguya's forces are
standing by at our rear.
All we need to do is push
in on them from behind,
and we've won.
We have to for Yoshida and
all the others who died.
[STAFF] Deputy-commander,
we've captured someone.
Is it one of the students?
Don't worry, let him go.
We haven't got a reason
to hold him here.
[STAFF]
No, this one was caught
sneaking in through
the rear gate.
[OHGI]
Sneaking in?
[gasps]
[OHGI]
Chigusa!
[OHGI] Sh-she's a collaborator
who reports directly to me.
Take her into one of
the unoccupied rooms,
and I'll hear her report there.
[MILLY]
Poor Nina.
I wonder if she's still
in the Ganymede hangar.
[RIVALZ] And Kallen's
part of this whole thing?
Man, this sucks!
What're we gonna do?
[SHIRLEY]
It's all right.
--[RIVALZ] Huh?
--[MILLY] Hm?
[SHIRLEY]
The Black Knights...
Or Zero, rather...
They absolutely won't
do anything to harm us.
But how can you be
so sure of that?
--[SUZAKU] Coward!
--[RIVALZ gasps]
[NUNNALLY whimpers]
--[MILLY] Huh?!
--[RIVALZ] Hm?
You've taken them
as your hostages?!
Some one-on-one fight this is!
You brought this all on yourself
when you rejected my bids
to join me as my ally.
Now you'll regret these foolish
moral standards you cling to!
Hey, isn't that the
black Knightmare
that's been all over
the news lately?
No way! Zero's not targeting
this building, is he?!
He can't be! He can't!
Because if he does...!
[SUZAKU] If I can get
close enough to him
to use the Harkens...
Zero!
Now!
What the--?!
[RAKSHATA giggles]
I anticipated they
wouldn't have adequate time
to come up with a
countermeasure for this.
Zero, remember your promise.
[ZERO] Yes, you may do with
the machine as you wish.
Zero!
You deceive the people who
trust you to the very end!
You betrayer!
Hmph.
I've no time to argue which
of us is the bigger hypocrite.
Farewell, Suzaku Kururugi.
[SUZAKU]
Damn you!
Their defenses are
strong, as expected.
Should you really be
treating this so casually?
Enemy reinforcements
are arriving.
If they start bombing
us, it's all over.
Huh. But we have a replenished
energy filler, haven't we?
[ZERO]
Tohdoh, I'm going to move in
on the government
bureau from above.
[TOHDOH]
Hm?
Isn't it risky to rely on the
abilities of that machine?
[ZERO]
I know that.
I'm just going to
create some confusion.
It appears to be...
[C.C.]
Yes. Aries Villa.
What?! How do you know that?!
[C.C.]
I'll tell you some day...
...when the time is right.
[CORNELIA]
Welcome, Zero.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[CORNELIA]
I figured you would show up here
as soon as you learned
about the air raid.
Now... Join us for
your welcome soirée!
Care for a dance?
[OHGI]
Chigusa.
Why did you come to
this battlefield?!
We need to find some
place safe for you.
Stay with me for now.
Uh... Huh..?
[sighs]
Look... I'm sorry
I hid this from you.
But everything I'm doing
is for the sake of peace!
If Zero succeeds in freeing
Japan from Britannia,
then we can finally be together!
Oh, stop before I puke!
[OHGI gasps]
Me together with
an Eleven like you?
What a horrible thought. Heh.
My name is Villetta Nu, and I am
a Knight of Honor of Britannia.
[OHGI groans]
So I see, Chigusa...
You've gotten your...
memory back...
Is it true?! Ohgi's been shot?!
[STAFF 2]
Yeah, the medic's with him now.
And was it that
woman who did it?!
[STAFF 2] We're still
not sure. We're searching
for her as we speak!
Wait!
Huh?
Don't tell anybody
else about Ohgi.
The news would
only rattle people.
Just find the girl and
bring her back here!
[STAFF 2]
Yes sir!
[RIVALZ] Oh! Now they've
even got Suzaku!
--[footsteps]
--[RIVALZ] Huh?
[footsteps continue]
I wonder what's
going on out there.
[NUNNALLY]
Now's your chance, please go!
[GROUP]
Huh?
Suzaku needs your help!
Go to him, please!
And we need his help.
He's the best hope we've got.
[STAFF A]
It's pitch black.
You'd never know if the
culprit was hiding in here.
[STAFF B]
Where's the light switch?
[BK STAFF A]
Dunno!
[STAFF B gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Zero! Princess Euphemia...
[CORNELIA]
...will be avenged!
What's wrong, Zero?!
The specs on this thing
are far superior to hers!
[CORNELIA]
You're just a weakling!
I have you!
I have you right
where I want you!
Your life is now in my hands!
Cornelia!
This is your judgment!
[CORNELIA groans]
[DARLTON]
Princess, it's me, Darlton.
[CORNELIA gasps]
Why, Darlton, why?
Don't be afraid.
I haven't come to
kill you, my lady.
Well, he made it.
[DARLTON] I'm here to deliver
you to Zero, Your Highness.
[gasps]
What have I done?!
Why, Princess?
[ZERO]
Thank you, Darlton.
[DARLTON]
Princess!
[door opens]
[NUNNALLY]
Uh?
Hello?
Oh, who's there?
Is that you, C.C.?
No, it's not.
[NUNNALLY]
Hm? But...
Nunnally...
I've come to take you with me.
[LELOUCH] Cornelia, the
second princess of the empire,
has fallen into my hands.
After I've questioned her about
the identity of my
mother's killer,
I only need to hold her
hostage, and I've won.
At last, for Nunnally's
sake as well,
I will obliterate Britannia!
The country that
abandoned us both!