[C.C.]
This is 2-D-4.
We are now entering Tokyo
Settlement-controlled airspace.
[ATC]
Roger.
Your flight objective here is
commercial advertising, correct?
[C.C.]
No change in that.
As filed, the duration of
our flight will be 14 hours.
[ATC] That is confirmed.
You are cleared for fly-over.
[C.C.]
Acknowledged. I appreciate it.
[URABE]
We're the only ones left now.
This is all that remains
of the Black Knights who,
along with Zero,
once struck terror in
the heart of Britannia.
Still, it's too soon
to give in to despair!
If Operation Flying Swallow
Four is successful, then...!
--[BLACK KNIGHTS] Yes.
--Forgive me. Here's to you.
To victory! Long live Japan!
[BLACK KNIGHTS]
Long live Japan!
[VILLETTA]
Lelouch.
Uh? Oh, not again.
You are persistent.
You're not going to
get away this time!
[STUDENT A] Hey, Lelouch,
about what you said--
Sorry! Catch ya later!
Lelouch, you come back here!
Vice Prez!
[STUDENT B]
Hope you get lucky.
Yeah, whatever!
[LELOUCH panting]
You lost the moment
you turned this into
a contest of strength and speed.
Aren't you overreacting?
I mean, this is just about
making up a P.E. class.
No! Quit cutting class, Lelouch!
I have more than
enough school credits
to pass, don't I?
[LELOUCH] Don't worry,
it's only colored smoke!
[VILLETTA]
Wait!
[MILLY]
Hey, Vice Prez, hang in there!
Uh! Thanks a lot!
What kind of student
president are you?!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Lost my head.
Lelouch...!
Heh!
[RIVALZ] Ow, are you
trying to kill me, coach?
--Rivalz?! But how did you...?
--[engine revs]
[LELOUCH] I need to borrow
your bike, Rivalz! See ya!
What're you up to now, Lulu?
[LELOUCH]
For crying out loud!
Can't they give me a break and
leave me alone after school?
But... they only do that because
you're always skipping
class, big brother.
Because I find them
insufferably boring.
Here, have some.
It's from Milly.
Uh...
[LELOUCH]
Whoa!
[ROLO]
I can't eat and steer!
You're right. I'm sorry.
[LELOUCH] It's been a year
since Britannian forces
crushed the Black Rebellion--
the revolt instigated by Zero.
Things have finally
quieted down,
even here in Area 11.
When the insurrection began,
all sorts of rumors were flying.
At one point, I considered
returning to the homeland
with my brother.
[ROLO] Did you hand in your
career guidance report yet?
Huh?
That's the reason
Ms. Villetta was so upset.
Oh...
So, what about college?
Well, I haven't decided yet.
I am sick and tired
of being a student.
But I'm not ready to get a job
and join the system, either.
A typical answer.
[LELOUCH] Besides, what could
I ever hope to attain
by entering the workforce?
Big corporations
and the nobility
would still be above me.
A structured, mature world.
I would simply be absorbed
into the hierarchy of adults.
We all need to understand that
this is not discrimination!
But rather,
it's differentiation!
The Elevens revealed
themselves to be a dangerous,
belligerent race!
They followed the
scoundrel, Zero,
and took up the name "Japanese"!
It's our duty as
Britannians to control
and educate them!
[LELOUCH] The Elevens lost.
They didn't have the strength.
If they'd only kept
quiet and behaved,
this place wouldn't
have been downgraded
to a re-education zone.
Zero... He was a fool.
No matter what you try,
the world is just a...
[STAFF A]
Viceroy Calares, please hurry,
the delegation from the
Chinese Federation is waiting.
I understand.
Are those O.S.I. people
going to carry it out?
Yes, at Babel Tower, my lord.
[CALARES sighs]
On today, of all days...
What could His
Majesty be thinking?
I seriously doubt that
the scattered remnants
of the Black Knights can do
anything to us at this point.
Besides... Zero is long dead.
Quit slackin' off,
lazy Eleven monkey!
[WORKER]
Y-Yes, sir!
[COMMAND AGENT A]
Target arriving, as predicted.
[STAFF A]
Ground foot patrol to main.
Sending I.D. numbers of
peripheral vehicles.
--[VEHICLE 1] Main to ground...
--[COMMAND AGENT B] Target now
entering fifth gate from B-3.
[COMMAND AGENT C] Do you
think she'll show this time?
I just know we can't
afford to fail.
We're taking a huge
risk by letting Lelouch
go to the settlement's
outer edge.
Oh, all right then.
You can come with me,
but I warn you,
you'll have to watch out.
Because today, I'm going
to be breaking the law.
Don't get caught!
[LELOUCH]
Heh. Cops don't scare me.
Why do this?
'Cause I mean, you're
not even doing this
for the money, are you?
[LELOUCH]
Need you ask?
It's because I wanna battle
more challenging opponents!
[LELOUCH] That's a lie. I do
this out of sheer boredom.
In short... I'm...
[elevator dings]
[CASINO GUESTS murmuring]
[BOXERS grunting, groaning]
[ANNOUNCER] Today's main
event is a brutal match
between brothers!
Which sibling will win--
the older one or the younger?!
We don't belong here. Let's go.
It's simple to figure
out. Just relax.
Uh?
Look there.
The Britannians, like ourselves,
are laughing and having fun.
The ones who are being
laughed at are the Elevens.
You pretend not to notice,
but in the end...
But then, why...?
I know, but it's the truth.
The Elevens lost twice.
First, with Prime Minister
Kururugi, and again, with Zero.
How could they rebel
when they don't
have the strength?
[WOMAN gasps]
[WOMAN]
I'm terribly sorry!
No, it's fine, don't worry.
[WOMAN] But I'm an Eleven,
and you're a Britannian student!
This is inexcusable!
[LELOUCH] All the more
reason to excuse you.
I hate having our social class
held over you like a sword.
[WOMAN]
It doesn't matter.
The powerless have no choice,
but to bear their lot in life.
Huh?
Regardless if their
oppressor is wrong.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
push your values on me.
I'm not interested.
[KALLEN]
I beg your pardon.
[KALLEN yelps]
C'mere, lemme take
a look at ya. Hm?
Hm, nice goods
you've got here.
Yes, Mr. King, we have a large,
quality catch of bunnies today.
[LELOUCH grunts]
You're wrong, sir,
I'm not for sale!
But you are for sale.
You should know by now,
losers don't have any rights!
Alert. Unforeseen
trouble occurring.
[COMMANDER]
Tsk!
Curse your own wretched birth
for not having been
born with power.
That's what His Majesty
always says, isn't it?
His Majesty...
[KING] The strong feed
upon and devour the weak.
That's the rule, kid!
The guy's Mafia, Lelouch!
What an arrogant display.
[KING]
Hm?
[LELOUCH]
Feeding upon the weak, are you?
This is the grownup world in
here, schoolboy, so get lost.
Then will the adult world
devour the student,
or is it the other way around?
Why don't we find out
the answer with this?
With chess?
[ROLO]
Big brother, don't!
Too late, fellas. Right, boys?
[GOONS laugh]
Students really don't know
much of anything, do they?
[LELOUCH]
That's not true, Mr. Black King.
[KING]
Hm?!
You're a famous chess player
in the gambling
arena, aren't you?
[KING]
So, you know who I am, huh?
[TAMAKI groans]
[growls] If Zero was here,
you wouldn't be acting so tough!
Do me a favor.
Don't say that
traitor's name again.
Hey, Zero didn't betray us!
Shut up, you stinkin' Eleven!
There has to be a
reason for what he did.
What reason? Why'd
the commander vanish
during the final decisive
battle like that?!
[PRISON GUARD]
Huh?
Stop it!
It serves no purpose.
Zero's dead, after all.
[gasps]
He's dead?
And that's checkmate.
Impossible!
[CASINO 1]
The student beat him!
[CASINO 2]
Black King lost!
[CASINO 3]
How could he lose so easily?
Looks like you're the one
who's been devoured here.
Damn. That's inconvenient.
How will I ever be able
to show my face in public
if word of this gets around?
I would never spread rumors.
No, schoolboy, not that.
What I'm saying is
that others will hear
how you cunningly cheated me.
I what?!
[KING]
Such a naughty little man...
Uh! Now wait a minute!
Cheat? But in chess,
how could you?
There's no way to do it!
Get him and hold him.
Now to whip up a little
evidence against the kid.
You filthy, lying adult!
Fair play doesn't win the
game. Learn that, schoolboy!
--Let him go!
--[rumbling]
[gasps]
Terrorists?!
[KING groans]
[KALLEN grunts]
[GOONS groan]
[URABE]
Move out!
[KALLEN]
Come on! This way!
What?! Hey!
Lelouch!
[rumbling]
An airship, huh?
Their final gasp.
[COMMANDER]
Office of Secret Intelligence,
initiate Operation
Valhalla Seven.
[AGENTS]
Yes, my lord!
[LELOUCH] What is this?!
What's happening?!
What?!
We welcome you
here to Area 11.
We didn't expect
an armed reception.
Especially after hearing
that Zero was dead.
Zero? You have the wrong idea.
I hoped it would offer you
and the other representatives
of the Chinese Federation
a better understanding
of us Britannians.
My...
An uncommonly straightforward
approach. Hm...?
[ATTENDANT A] May we have
what you're carrying, sir?
Our security is perfect.
You don't need to carry
that antique weapon here.
[gasps]
Xing-ke! That was rude of you!
Please forgive me.
But I hoped it would
offer you and the other
Britannians a
better understanding
of the Chinese Federation.
--Why you...
--[rumbling]
Huh?
--[XING-KE grunts]
--[rumbling]
[KALLEN yelps]
[CASINO GUESTS yelling]
Huh? What?
[ROLO]
Big brother, this way!
[LELOUCH]
Hey!
No! Wait a minute!
[rumbling]
We what?! Lost sight
of the target?!
Yes, that is correct.
We will be going in now.
[URABE]
Understood.
[BABEL COMM 1] The terrorists
attacking Babel Tower
appear well equipped.
They're armed with
several Knightmares.
[BABEL COMM 2] At commencement
of the operation,
perimeter cleaning complete.
Good. Now enter
the seventh sequence.
[BABEL COMM 3]
Commander, Viceroy Calares is--
[COMMANDER] Pay no attention
to that low-level bureaucrat.
Our orders come directly
from the emperor himself!
[BABEL COMM 3]
Yes, my lord.
[MAN 1]
Elevens can take the stairs!
[MAN 2]
Get out, we're overloaded!
[MAN 3]
Stop pushing!
[LELOUCH]
Terrorists?
What are leftover fragments of
the Black Knights doing here?
[LELOUCH yelps]
Huh?!
Britannian military!
[LELOUCH, ROLO yelp]
[ROLO gasps]
[CROWD groaning, screaming]
Filthy Britannians!
Sorry, I wasn't able to bring
him here like we planned!
[BLACK KNIGHT 1]
Don't sweat it.
Urabe and the others are
looking for him right now.
Understood!
Rolo, this way!
[ROLO panting]
[LELOUCH grunts]
[LELOUCH]
What the hell's going on?
That Knightmare earlier...
Was it trying to...
Lelouch, what'll we do now?
Don't worry. We'll be
all right, I promise you.
I'll get us out of here.
[gasps]
Yeah, I'm-I'm sure.
We'll be fine.
[gasps] Rolo!
[ROLO yelps]
[gasps]
[LELOUCH yells]
[gasping]
Lelouch!
And now, Lulu's giving
all of his same
bad habits to Rolo!
Admit it, Shirley.
You're worried about
your darling Lulu.
No, I am not!
There she goes again!
Uh!
Whatever...
[LELOUCH]
R-Rolo...
Rolo!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] I'm out of range.
What do I do now?
At this rate, we'll both be...!
No! I have to try and save him!
The least I should be able to
do is save my only brother!
Even I ought to have enough
strength in me to do that.
I have to!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] Terrorists are
responsible for this?
But... Elevens were killed, too!
[LELOUCH gags]
[LELOUCH gasps]
Are these people
still counting on Zero
to rescue them?! Uh?!
The Black Knights!
What do I do?
Will they kill me?
Even if I run...
[C.C.]
Lelouch.
[gasps]
I came to get you
out of here, Lelouch.
I'm on your side, an ally.
And your sworn
enemy is Britannia.
Huh?
We have a contract.
You and I are both accomplices.
[LELOUCH]
Contract? Accomplices?
[C.C.] I'm the only one who
knows you. The real you.
What does she mean, the real me?
--[gunshot]
--[LELOUCH gasps]
Le-Lelouch...
Hey, are you all right?!
[gasps]
Why are soldiers--
[LELOUCH gasps]
No, hold on! What are you--
[WOMAN screams]
Stop it, that
woman's still alive!
[gunshots]
[COMMANDER] You've served
your function well.
Good Lelouch Lamperouge.
[LELOUCH] Function?!
What're you talking about?!
We've had our eye on you
for a very long
time now, young man.
Wakes up at 6:59 AM.
From 7:12 AM, watches the
news with his little brother
while eating breakfast.
No ideological deviations
with the program he watches.
8:45 AM, goes to class.
Doesn't attend his
morning homeroom
or first period class.
Instead, he reads on the roof.
During his second period...
Those are things...
I've done today...
I prefer to think of it
as a pet diary, or...
...bait journal.
Bait journal?
[COMMANDER]
Or call it a trap, if you wish.
For that witch. All to
lure C.C. out of hiding!
No, wait, please!
What's going on?!
Boy, I'll have you know
that I am a Baron.
I'm through wasting
words on bait like you!
Now, time to dispose of you.
And there won't be
any witnesses left.
Dispose...?
Is this... the end for me?
Without even knowing why?
So matter-of-factly?
[LELOUCH] To hell with that!
Power! If I only had power!
Power to escape this place!
Power not to lose the world...!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH]
What... What is this?
[C.C.]
You desire power?
[LELOUCH] That voice...
The girl who was shot?
[C.C.] You already possess
the power you seek.
It's merely imprisoned
within a cage of amnesia.
Remember...
Remember who you really are!
The power of the king!
[C.C.]
Now... let the seal...
...be broken!
[LELOUCH]
I see now.
Persistent irritation
that pricked me
like thorns in my everyday life.
Yes... Heh!
It was all the phony
memories implanted in me!
[LELOUCH]
But I remember now... I am...!
I am...!
I am... Zero!
[SUZAKU] Lelouch. I'm not
asking for forgiveness.
After all, we're
friends, aren't we?
[LELOUCH] Yes... That's your
answer, isn't it, Suzaku?!
[LELOUCH]
Before you dispose of me,
I'd like you to
answer a question.
[PURPLE SOLDIER 1]
That girl's still alive!
[PURPLE SOLDIER 2]
Impossible!
She was shot through the heart!
If being powerless
is so terribly wrong,
then does having
power make you right?
Do you find vengeance evil?
What's your value of
friendship? Is it justice?
Heh, there is no
justice or evil.
The only truth that's
left for you, bait,
is the simple reality of death.
[LELOUCH]
I see.
Then that reality is all that
remains for you, as well.
I, Lelouch vi Britannia,
command you!
All of you... die!
[COMMANDER]
It-It can't be!
[PURPLE SOLDIERS]
Yes, Your Highness!
[laughs]
[gunshots]
[bodies thudding]
[LELOUCH]
Ever since that day, my heart
simply couldn't accept it.
This fake life I was
never able to fit into.
All the time that was lost.
These false memories
planted in me,
giving me a life
as one of the herd.
And yet...
The truth continues to
guide me toward itself.
That's right!
It wasn't me who was
wrong! It was the world!
The world has to change.
So I will change it.
[URABE] We've been waiting
for you, Master Zero!
Please, give us your orders!
[LELOUCH]
Very well...
Because, after all, I am Zero!
The one who will
crush the world...!
...and the one who will
re-create the world anew!
[SUZAKU]
Yes... Your Majesty.
I have no intention of assigning
this task to anyone else.
The one who will kill Zero...
...shall be me.
[LELOUCH] I can't forgive them!
I mustn't forgive them!
My memories are my own
personal and individual reality!
They are the truth,
and that truth defines me!
Someone trampled them.
I was tamed like a domestic
animal then looked down upon
as mere bait. The time
for payback has come!
Now, I'll give Britannia
something to remember.
The true meaning of Zero's
return to this world!
Because I no longer have need
for their deceptive rule!