[C.C.] To this day, no one has
understood the urgent desires
and heaving emotions within
the young Britannian Lelouch,
despite his expectations
for the final outcome.
Before he can go forward,
there is one more enemy
Lelouch must confront.
However, this one is
different than all others.
For this enemy is
human nature itself.
Hope and atonement.
Freedom and solitude.
That mass of matter and
energy known as the world...
Keeps on flowing forward despite
the desires of any one man.
[V.V.] Charles, have you learned
anything by becoming emperor?
Yes, big brother.
All people are liars.
And this vast nation we call
Britannia never changes.
[V.V.]
That may be true,
but it's just human
nature, isn't it?
[EMPEROR]
Perhaps you're right about that.
[V.V.] Charles you won't forget,
will you? Our contract?
[EMPEROR] I know. To kill God
and smash this world of lies...
[ROLO]
That was a close call,
big brother. Shirley
regained her memory.
She had a gun, and she
was coming after you.
[LELOUCH] I see. So you were
the one who killed her.
Yes, I did it for you; I have
to eliminate your enemies.
[LELOUCH]
Rolo...
[ROLO]
What, big brother?
You handled it very well.
If it weren't for you,
everybody would've known
about my secret.
Exactly and it isn't just your
secret anymore, brother.
[LELOUCH] True. So, shall we
destroy the Geass Order now?
[ROLO]
Uh?!
[LELOUCH]
The Black Knights can wipe out
the source of Geass
once and for all.
[ROLO]
Big brother, we can't.
There are still
Geass users there.
If we keep avoiding
this, we'll never win.
Remember, this is for our
happiness. For both of us.
For both of us?
That's right. V.V. has
begun to suspect you.
[LELOUCH]
Are you afraid of V.V.?
[ROLO] Well, he was
the one who found me.
Still, Lelouch, can I
really believe in you?
[LELOUCH]
Of course.
We're the only brothers
we have, aren't we?
[CORNELIA]
Are you going to kill me?
Or control me with your Geass?
Like you did to Euphy?
To prove your
sister's innocence,
you renounced your position gave
up everything. That's inspiring.
[CORNELIA grunts]
You made me think, Cornelia.
Is there any more splendid
relationship in this entire
world than that of
loyal siblings?
[DOCTOR] Organ failure
due to gunshot wounds
and loss of blood.
[SUZAKU] Shirley. You're
saying that she shot herself?
[DOCTOR]
Yes. Apparently on impulse.
[SHIRLEY'S MOM crying]
Suicide? She couldn't...
Has anyone seen Lelouch?
[RIVALZ]
Mm-mm.
[SHIRLEY'S MOM cries]
No!
[KANON] I see.
She was a friend of yours.
[NINA] Yes. Milly just
told me about it.
[KANON]
Were you close?
[NINA] I'm not sure. She was
just always so cheerful.
To be honest,
she kind of bothered me.
[KANON] I see. Perhaps you were
envious of her happiness?
[NINA] Maybe Maybe that
was it. That's why...
I never imagined that
I would cry over her!
[KANON] Nina as long
as you can shed tears,
then you're all right.
[C.C.] I can't believe Lelouch.
Who does he think I am?
Leaving me behind here
like I was a messenger
girl or something.
[C.C.]
What?! Ugh, hardly.
I'm just really worried that
he's forgotten our contract.
Anyway, what are you
planning to do?
How long are you going
to stay inside of--
C.C.
[C.C.]
Hm?
[LELOUCH] I have finally
located where the Order is.
Jeremiah and Rolo provided
key information.
We're going to send in the
Zero Squad and wipe it out.
[C.C.] Wipe it out?
Weren't you going to use it?
They're not a military group.
They just do research
into Geass--
We'll crush them!
Tell me what happened.
[LELOUCH] The power of
Geass which they unleashed
caused Shirley's death.
She was killed by Geass!
[C.C.] And so now you're
going to wipe out the Order?
As atonement.
To make sure the same thing
doesn't happen to anyone else.
You said Geass is the
power of the king.
There can be only one king,
so I alone shall have it.
I will erase Rolo. I'll erase
Geass from all the others.
Its power to make people
sinful will be obliterated
from this world!
I owe that to Shirley.
At the very least!
And are you going to
erase me, as well?
[LELOUCH]
You know I can't do that.
You are eternally young.
And immortal.
V.V. is also eternally young.
And also immortal.
I'll neutralize him
and leave him helpless.
And there's always the method
that Clovis used on you.
Besides, I want to see if you're
really loyal to me now.
Since you were once the leader
of the Order we're fighting.
That was a long time ago.
And I was just window dressing.
I never had real
power like V.V...
Still.
We've been accomplices,
haven't we?
[LELOUCH] The order will be
wiped out which will test you.
[C.C.] I'm prepared to
see it through to the end.
[LELOUCH] Good, because
there's one thing more:
I want to know the details
of our contract.
What is it you want
from all this?
[C.C.] That has nothing
to do with the mission;
I have no intention
of
[LELOUCH]
Hmpf! Willful woman!
Yes, that's right. That's
exactly what makes me C.C.
[PRIEST B] Bartley and
the others are one thing,
but what do we do about
Princess Cornelia?
[PRIEST C] Shouldn't we at
least contact His Majesty?
[V.V.] Hm. I wonder if Charles
knew about Cornelia's actions.
Or if he didn't...
[PRIEST B]
Huh?
[PA VOICE]
Director V.V., we have
the scheduled transmission
from Lord Jeremiah.
[V.V.] Right. Can you
patch it through?
Surprised to see me?
[V.V.]
Uh.
[LELOUCH]
So, you're V.V...
Lelouch!
[PRIEST A] How can he have
access to Jeremiah's network?!
[PRIEST D]
Where's the signal from?
[PRIEST C] Area 11. Looks
like he's inside Ashford.
[LELOUCH] I'm sure I need no
introduction at this point,
so I'll just start with
direct questions.
Was it you who
kidnapped Nunnally
during the battle for Tokyo?
Also, did you put Suzaku
and I and the others
on Kamine Island to observe us?
[V.V.]
Yes, that's correct.
But the fact that you're
asking these questions
means you've regained all of
your memories, doesn't it?
That's right, I am Zero.
[V.V.] Then C.C. must be with
you. Can you hand her over?
We'll let you go free if you do.
It's too late for that!
I hereby declare war against
you, with no mercy!
[V.V.] Oh yeah! But by the
time you get here from Area 11,
we'll have moved
to another place--
[explosion]
[PA VOICE]
Director V.V.! Knightmares!
What?!
[PA GUY]
I think it's the Black Knights!
[C.C.] V.V.'s current
location is verified.
Strike force,
encircle point alpha-7!
[V.V.]
I see. So, that's how it is.
That's right. I'm glad you
gave me a bit of your time.
You just had to let down
your guard for a moment.
Since you believed
I was in Area 11,
you thought you had
time to escape.
That's why you're
trapped now.
V.V., the one who shall render
judgement here is me!
[ALL screaming]
[V.V.] Load the research
data into the Eject Dart
and prepare the device;
you know which one I mean.
[PRIEST A] Director, you're
facing them personally?
I need to buy you time
to escape with the data.
Besides, I have to teach some
discipline to Marianne's child.
I never would have guessed.
I mean, that you were a
royal princess, Nunnally.
[NUNNALLY] Forgive me for
hiding things from you.
[KALLEN]
Same for me.
[NUNNALLY] It's so nostalgic,
talking about Ashford Academy.
They told me I wouldn't
see Milly and the others.
So Suzaku is the only one
I've been able to talk to.
They also said my
brother has vanished.
No one knows where he is.
Tell me, what sort of brother
was Lelouch for you?
Huh?
[KALLEN] I used to have
a brother, too, so,
that's why I ask.
[NUNNALLY] I'm happy
just to have someone
to talk to about Lelouch.
Excuse me, please.
[KALLEN]
Mm?
[SUZAKU]
Viceroy Nunnally,
I'd like to borrow prisoner
1-0-7 from you.
[NUNNALLY]
Uh.
[ALL screaming]
[STAFF groaning]
[BLACK KNIGHT A]
Sub-commander Kinoshita,
something's wrong here!
This isn't a Britannian
military installation.
Uh. Yeah, you're right.
They haven't put up
any resistance at all.
They don't even seem
to have weapons.
[ZERO]
Use extreme prejudice!
But, sir...!
[ZERO] Britannia has
been colluding with traitors
in the Chinese Federation.
This lab is developing
immortal warriors
whose purpose
is to destroy us!
I won't let them violate
the sanctity of life!
The researchers and their
data are to be wiped out!
We don't know where the subjects
of the immortality
research are hidden!
Therefore, encircle point
alpha-7 and destroy everything!
Burn it to the ground! Any
experimental subjects found
are to be sealed inside
of high pressure casing!
I will investigate each
one of them personally!
[BARTLEY] Have you found
Princess Cornelia yet?!
We have to use this
chance to save everyo--
[ALL screaming]
That man there, wasn't
he working with Clovis?
[STAFF A]
Director C.C.!
You've come back to us!
[STAFF B]
Please save us, C.C.!
[C.C. gasps]
Your Highness, Prince Clovis...
The eternally young, immortal
woman you wished to present
to His Majesty. It would
seem that he was already
aware of her
existence. Please...
Please forgive me,
Your Highness...
We never should've involved
ourselves with that witch.
[DIETHARD]
Yes,
Zero's gone to attack a
Britannian research facility.
He's kept the location
and mission secret.
More of those
clandestine activities?
And now that the Saudis
have been subjugated
we must ratify the united states
charter as quickly as possible.
It's true that more factions
are caving in to Britannia,
so we need to move very
quickly as you say.
[XING-KE] But there's positive
movement as well.
Italy and Poland have
come over to our side.
We need to speak to Zero
as soon as he returns.
[DIETHARD]
Understood.
[DIETHARD] This is what
Zero wants, isn't it?
Yes. We have to
maintain tight secrecy
around his activities
and his very existence.
[DIETHARD] Then I want you to go
after deputy-commander Ohgi.
[SAYOKO]
Huh?
[DIETHARD]
He's been acting strangely
since the meeting a few
days ago. No. He's been
hiding something from us
for a long time before that.
[AIRPORT STAFF sighs] Flights
to the Chinese Federation
right now are cancelled...
[VILLETTA] I belong to the
Office of Secret Intelligence.
[AIRPORT STAFF]
Th-he one that reports
directly to His Majesty?!
[VILLETTA]
Right. I believe you have
special flights for
diplomatic purposes.
[AIRPORT STAFF]
Yes ma'am we do.
[VILLETTA] Now that Lelouch has
roped even Jermiah into this...
For Zero's sake, if
the deputy-commander
is collaborating with
the enemy, then...
[VILLETTA]
I must kill Ohgi Kaname!
[MORI]
Huh?
What are children
doing here?
Uh... Hm?
What the...?!
Ugh! My hand! [grunting]
What the devil are
you doing, Mori?!
It's not me!
I can't control it!
Uh? It's Geass?
That power means it's...
Big brother Rolo!
Hey, I miss all you guys:
how have you been?
The new guy.
Your name's Rolo, isn't it?
Are you one of them?
I have nothing to
do with them now.
As long as I keep following
my brother, I'm all right.
[LELOUCH laughs]
Once he corners V.V.,
I'll simply detonate the bomb I
planted in Rolo's knightmare.
My funeral offering to
Shirley will be Rolo's life!
He will atone for
what he did to her!
What?!
The Siegfried!
[JEREMIAH]
Impossible!
[LELOUCH]
Jermiah! Isn't that unit...?!
Yes. Since it works on
direct bio-connect...
The only one who can
use it beside me is...!
[V.V.]
Heh.
[LELOUCH]
I thought so!
You surprise me, V.V.!
[LELOUCH] The observer
becomes the perpetrator!
[V.V.] Y'know, I sort of
liked you, Lelouch.
Because you reminded
me of Charles.
[C.C.]
I can't believe it...
He's using the
Siegfried unit here?!
[LELOUCH] Get out of here!
You're the one he's after!
[V.V.]
Oh?
[JEREMIAH]
Hold it right there, V.V.!
[ROLO]
Please, just surrender.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
You're just a bunch of
traitors, aren't you!
V.V., I swear I'll tear you
out of that thing myself!
All units: attack!
Yes, Your Majesty!
[laughs]
[LELOUCH growls] That spinning
shield is powerful!
Marianne's son is getting
carried away with himself!
[JEREMIAH]
That machine
was made so that I
could prove my loyalty!
Jeremiah, I thought that you had
a personal grudge against Zero?
I did! Because I thought
he was a mere commoner
preventing me from
serving the royal family.
But now I know who he is, and I
know that by serving him...
I am serving my lady, Marianne!
[V.V.]
Even you...!
You dare speak
her name to me!
[BLACK KNIGHT RADIO]
Send out all remaining units!
It looks like that
monster outside
is piloted by their leader!
[KALLEN]
Shirley?!
[SUZAKU]
According to the forensics,
she committed suicide.
[KALLEN]
She'd never do that!
Suzaku, you know
that, don't you?!
[SUZAKU] Yeah, I do. Which means
that if somebody murdered her...
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Yes. Lelouch...
[LELOUCH grunts]
[LELOUCH] Rolo! Can you get
to the Siegfried somehow?
I'm not able to use my Geass
to do time stops on V.V...
[LELOUCH] You just need
to grab onto the unit.
I have a plan after that.
Okay, I'll do my best.
[LELOUCH] Rolo, the bomb I
planted on the Vincent is ready!
It'll destroy the Siegfried
and you in one blast.
[ROLO]
I have to try!
For big brother!
And now it's Rolo's turn.
You've lied to me just like
all the others, haven't you?
Even knowing that your
Geass won't work on me...
Oh, yeah!
[PRIEST A]
Director V.V.,
we've finished preparations to
escape with the research data.
Shall we take it to
the E.U. for now?
[V.V.] Yes. I'll join you after
I've finished things here.
Now I know how to capture C.C.,
so all we need to do
is escape and regroup,
then Charles and I can put
an end to this for good.
I just have to grab it!
You are a failed experiment,
don't you know that?
Your heart stops every
time you use your Geass.
That means you're defective. You
could conk out at any moment.
Not yet! If I eject them...!
Oh, yeah!
[ROLO]
I've done it, big brother!
[screams]
[V.V. laughs]
[LELOUCH]
Well done, Rolo!
Now, it's time for goodbye!
[LELOUCH grunts]
[V.V.] Who? Who could know the
Siegfrieg's only weak point?
[V.V. growls]
So, your name is V.V.?
You were mistaken
when you treated me like
an incompetent weakling.
[ROLO gasps]
[ROLO]
Forgive me, Big Brother!
[LELOUCH]
No, it's all right.
[LELOUCH] I never expected
Cornelia to be here!
The Siegfried's shields are
all down! Direct attack!
[V.V.]
Uh... Uh!
Now you're going to suffer,
for what you did to Euphy!
The source...
[LELOUCH, CORNELIA]
...of Geass!
[V.V.] It's no use! The
Siegfried is finished!
Uh!
It's you, Lelouch!
You are an abomination!
[JEREMIAH]
Come, Your Highness!
[PRIEST A]
The Siegfried!
[PRIEST B]
Director V.V.!
[PRIEST C] Calm down! Remember,
director V.V. cannot be killed.
He can always use the Twilight
Gate on the lowest level.
If we just get the research data
away from here, then we...
[PRIEST A]
Ah!
[PRIEST B]
Is that...?!
[PRIEST C]
Huh?! Lady C.C.!
[C.C.]
Forgive me.
This is my personal sin
for having neglected you.
At last I shall put an end
to the lineage of Geass.
So be it. Perhaps, this is
how Lelouch and I should...
[SUZAKU] All of the evidence
and testimony imply
that Lelouch is innocent...
But in my heart, I've known
all along that Lelouch was the
culprit. That he was Zero.
[KALLEN]
I don't know who Zero is!
I told you that when
I was captured.
[SUZAKU]
Enough of that!
To prevent another
death like Shirley's...
Nothing is off limits;
not anymore!
And that includes Refrain.
[KALLEN gasps]
[LELOUCH]
The target has fled inside!
I'll look for him, starting
on the lowest level!
Rolo, you search from
the top down! Kinoshita!
Take command and sweep
the middle levels!
[V.V. sighs, groans]
Lelouch How dare you!
I'm glad you came
after all... Charles.
The most splendid
relationship in the world
is that of loyal siblings.
[EMPEROR]
Big brother, is it true
you were the one who sent
an assassin after Lelouch?
[V.V.]
Yes. And thanks to that,
I've been the victim
of his assassins.
But I've also learned something.
That Lelouch is Zero.
That he even tricked Nunnally.
You lied to me once
again, big brother.
[KINOSHITA] This is as barbaric
as the Britannians!
Was it really necessary to
shoot children? Was it?
I'm picking up signs of life.
Have you returned to the
point where you began? V.V.!
What's this?! Dammit!
This is what happened
on Kamine Island!
[gasps] How was I pulled
out of the Shinkiro?
Where is this place? It's not
an illusion or a hologram.
[EMPEROR]
That is correct!
[LELOUCH gasps]
[EMPEROR] And knight mares
are such inelegant things.
Especially in the face of this
system: the Sword of Akasha!
[gasps] It's you...!
[EMPEROR] Lelouch, my son!
The time has come at last!
The time for final redemption!
[LELOUCH] How did the
Emperor bring me here?!
Dammit, I have to
think this through!
If he did this, he must
know that I'm Zero!
So there's no reason
to hide it anymore!
The best plan is to use my
Geass to make him my servant.
Then I won't need to capture
V.V. and trade him for Nunnally.
But his own Geass and
this place stand in my way!
So what are my options?!
It's all or nothing now!
This is a once in a lifetime
chance! I have to seize it!