[PALACE GUARD] Announcing
Prince Lelouch vi Britannia!
Seventeenth heir to the Royal
Britannian Imperial throne!
[NOBLEMAN A]
I heard Empress Marianna
was killed inside of
the Britannian palace.
[NOBLEMAN B]
There's no way terrorists
could've gotten in there.
[NOBLEMAN C] Which means that
the real assassins must've--
[NOBLEMAN D]
Sh! Beware, my friend.
You'll regret it if anyone
hears that kind of talk
around the palace.
[NOBLEMAN E]
And yet the boy remains.
Even though his mother is dead.
[NOBLEMAN G]
It's over.
And the Ashford family who
stood behind them is finished,
as well.
[NOBLEWOMAN H]
And his sister, the princess?
[NOBLEMAN A] I understand
she was shot in the legs.
[NOBLEMAN C]
And that she lost her sight.
[NOBLEMAN D] Blindness caused
by trauma, though, isn't it?
[NOBLEMAN F]
No difference.
Now, she can't even be
married off for political gain.
Hail, Your Majesty! My mother,
the empress, is dead!
Old news. What of it?
What of it?!
[EMPEROR]
You sought an audience
with the emperor of Britannia
simply to inform me of that?
Send the next one in.
I have no time for
these childish games.
[LELOUCH]
Father!
[GUARDS]
Yes, Your Majesty!
Why didn't you keep
mother out of harm's way?!
You're the emperor!
The greatest man in this
nation, if not the world!
You should've protected her!
And now you don't
even visit Nunnally!
I've no use for that weakling.
That weakling?
[EMPEROR] That is what
it means to be royalty.
Then I don't wanna
be your heir.
I give up my claim
to the throne!
[CROWD gasping]
I'm sick of the
fighting and scheming
over who will succeed you,
Father! I've had enough!
[EMPEROR]
You are dead.
You have always
been dead to me,
dead from the moment
you were born.
Who gave you the
fine clothes you wear,
a comfortable home, the food
you eat, and your very life?
All of those,
I have given to you!
In short, you are nothing to me
because you have never existed.
Yet you dare to speak
such foolishness to me!
[squeals]
[EMPEROR]
Lelouch!
You are dead, therefore you
are not entitled to any rights.
I am sending you
and Nunnally to Japan.
As prince and princess, you will
serve well as bargaining tools.
[LLOYD] It's a 7th-generation
Knightmare Frame,
making its abilities
far greater than normal.
[CORNELIA] I understand that the
Lancelot's pilot is an Eleven.
That's correct, an
honorary Britannian.
However--
I'm promoting this man from
private to warrant officer.
That should satisfy him.
I'm trying to win without having
to rely too much on the numbers.
[EUPHEMIA] Those who risk
their lives on the battlefield
are the ones who
deserve to rule.
I understand the theory,
Sister. But still...
[SUZAKU] Sorry you have to sit
here watching me do my homework.
[CECILE]
Oh, don't worry about it.
You've never attended
a regular school before,
so it can't be avoided.
[SUZAKU] The guys on the student
council are helping me, too,
but... it's still hard.
[CECILE giggles]
To be perfectly honest with you,
I've been a little bit worried.
It's supposed to be
a liberal school,
but I was afraid you
weren't fitting in well.
Me too, I was expecting that.
But I happened to run
into an old friend there,
and he smoothed
everything out for me.
Be sure you never take
that friend for granted.
If your friendship continues,
your reunion won't
have been coincidence,
it will have been predestined.
Okay.
Anyway, please try one of these.
Uh. Thank you, I will.
[CECILE]
I'd like your opinion of them.
There's jam?
Yes, I just happened to get
some lovely blueberries.
[LLOYD] All right, everyone!
Pack it up! Pack it up!
We're done today!
Don't do anymore!
Hip-hip-hoo-rayyyy!
That's all, folks!
[SUZAKU]
Uh... umm...
[CECILE chuckles]
[CECILE]
Go to school.
Classes might be over for
the day, but it's important
to meet your friends and
have a social life, too.
[SHIRLEY] Say, can I ask
you something important?
[KALLEN]
Hm? Sure, what is it?
[SHIRLEY] Kallen, are you
hiding something from us?
[KALLEN]
Huh?
[SHIRLEY] If it's
something too personal.
[KALLEN]
No. What're you talking about?
You can tell me. I promise
I won't be shocked or upset.
Well, the thing is, I
happened to see you before.
[KALLEN grunts]
You're going out
with Lulu, right?!
Lulu?
The other day.
I saw you outside!
[KALLEN]
Oh! No, no, no!
That was all his doing!
His doing?!
No, wait, it wasn't like that...
I don't get it. You were trying
so hard to catch the cat before.
No, that wasn't it.
Besides, it's not like
we kissed or anything.
Or anything?! Then you
stopped short of doing it?!
Will you quit imagining things!
You don't understand the
circumstances one bit!
[MILLY] But an arranged
marriage is so...
I understand how
much you want to
re-establish the
Ashford family.
But, Mother, it's just that--
[NINA]
Ah! I've divided it!
[DARLTON] The Saitama ghetto
is now completely surrounded.
The Yamato Alliance's hideout
is located somewhere in here.
Half the people in
this neighborhood
are cooperating with them.
So, if we proceed now--
What'll be the effect
on production?
[DARLTON] Primary sector output
should decrease by 0.2%.
Within expectations,
you mean. All right.
All of you here participated
in the Shinjuku disaster,
is that correct?
Yes, and we're indebted
to you, Princess Cornelia,
for your mercy--
[CORNELIA]
That's not what I'm asking!
Do you think the
conditions are similar?
[FORMER OFFICER 1]
Huh?
To those in Shinkjuku.
Military authorities report
that they have surrounded
the Saitama ghetto, a known
hiding place for terrorists.
Viceroy Cornelia is
also on the scene,
and entry to that
area is restricted.
[C.C. chuckles]
Oh? Well, what has
you looking so serious?
It appears that a
full-scale assault
will be launched in two hours.
Consequently, power
will be shut off...
News is one thing, but why are
we broadcasting the start time?
Because they're trying
to provoke Zero.
[CORNELIA] Zero is a criminal
with a flair for the theatrical.
I've recreated
the same conditions
that existed in Shinjuku
in order to draw him out.
If he's the overconfident type,
I predict he'll come
here to try and kill me.
[FORMER OFFICER 1]
Viceroy.
You'd really risk your
own life like this?.
What you fail to understand
is the war is a struggle
between pride and life.
[C.C.] You're not falling for
the enemy's provocation?
They went to such trouble
to invite me, though.
Besides, there's something I'd
like to ask Cornelia personally.
[C.C.]
Destroying Britannia
or discovering who
murdered your mother.
Which is more important to you?
[LELOUCH]
The two are of equal importance.
The royal family members are
competing with each other
to see who will
ascend the throne
and become the next ruler.
Or rather, they're
being forced to fight.
By that man.
But the very thing you
hate is the same thing,
that makes Britannia strong.
The royal heir who is best fit
to become the next ruler
of Britannia is the
last one left standing.
[LELOUCH]
Exactly.
The weak ones lose,
and they're cast aside.
Britannia's that
kind of nation.
That kind of world.
Survival of the fittest is
the most basic rule of all.
[LELOUCH] If that's true,
then what happens to Nunnally?!
Should I simply give up on my
sister because she's frail?!
I refuse to accept that!
I'll wipe out that
sort of world myself!
[gasps]
[SUZAKU humming]
[KALLEN] Like I said, there's
nothing between Lelouch and I.
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch?
Anyway, that's how it is!
There's nothing's going on.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
Um... where's Lelouch?
I don't know where he is,
and I don't give a damn!
[SUZAKU]
Uh?
You can't go, Lelouch.
You need to fulfill your
part of our bargain,
so I won't have you
dying before that.
[LELOUCH]
Notice that what you're saying
and what you're doing
are contradictory.
Oh, I won't kill you.
I'm merely going to shoot you
in the leg to quiet you down.
Now I get it.
You're unable to use Geass
yourself, aren't you?
[C.C.]
Uh.
I'm not surprised,
I suspected as much.
You obviously wouldn't
have asked me to do it
if you could've
done it yourself.
[C.C.] Do you honestly think
you can threaten me with a gun?
Yes, I do.
[LELOUCH]
Until I met you, I was dead.
An impotent corpse existing
behind a false guise of life.
A life in which
I did nothing real.
Day to day, I merely went
through the motions of living,
as if I were a zombie,
and I always had the feeling
that I was gradually dying.
If I'm condemned to go back
to that, then I'd rather--
[C.C.]
Stop it!
I see now.
It's life without meaning.
And a life like that...
Oh my god!
Why the hell did you do that?!
Even children are here!
What's going on?!
We haven't done anything!
[CAPTAIN]
That's exactly why!
The people of this ghetto
refuse to report the terrorists!
You hide them! Cover for them!
That's treason against
a suzerain state!
We're done sweeping
away those in charge.
It's nearly time to set
our plan into motion.
So, shall we begin?
Right!
Attention, all forces!
Commence eradication
of the Saitama ghetto!
[DARLTON] All forces, assume
level one battle stations!
[JEREMIAH]
I don't understand.
Why won't Princess Cornelia
order us to attack, as well?!
She won't because
Orange is here.
Just be thankful that you
haven't been disposed of.
You're to blame for this.
It's due to you that
our careers are over!
You're wrong! Zero's
the one who did it!
[KEWELL]
That again? Hmph.
[VILLETTA] Zero... Could that
student be working with him?
[COMM 1]
Suppression of area 4, complete.
eighth and eleventh
mechanized infantry companies
are sweeping north and
south in a pincer movement.
[LELOUCH]
Always the same.
Cornelia replaces Clovis...
yet Britannia never changes.
[PILOT A]
What unit are you from?
Your unit name
and I.D., soldier!
Private Dario Torres, sir,
with third
reconnaissance company.
I obtained this item from
one of the terrorists.
Could I ask you to
please transmit it
to headquarters for me, sir?
[PILOT A]
A disk, huh?
Well, I still need to
verify your I.D. first.
Right, understood, but
before we do that, sir,
I'd like to borrow your
Sutherland, so hand it over.
[PILOT A]
Uh.
Sure, no problem.
Just take good care of it.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
[TERRORIST A]
It's hopeless.
[LEADER] Can't we break through
along the Sai-Kyo line?
[TERRORIST C]
They've got armor blocking it.
[TERRORIST D]
We can't use back roads, either.
[LEADER] Any reinforcements
from Akabane or Jujoh?
[TERRORIST C] One man might
get through, but not a group!
[MAN]
Izumi!
[LEADER] Damn. Any word from
the Toda or Kawaguchi districts?
[MAN]
Forget that! Listen!
[LEADER]
Huh?!
[ZERO]
This... is Zero.
Zero?
[TERRORIST A]
Zero? You mean--?
[ZERO]
I assume all of you have heard
about the Shinjuku incident.
Do what I say,
and you will be saved.
[TERRORISTS gasping]
[COMM 1]
B-12, suppression complete.
[COMM 2]
F-7, no sign of the enemy.
[COMM 3]
D-24, 87% complete.
[COMM 1] Powadon team,
change course to 5-1-6.
[POWADON]
Yes, my lord. Moving to 5-1-6.
No response at all.
This guy Zero might turn
out to be a no-show.
[SUBORDINATE]
Guess he's just another
run-of-the mill terrorist.
They came! They really came!
Just like Zero said they would!
Now then, shall
I drag Cornelia out
or should I make an opening?
R-1, R-2, maintain distance.
Draw them back to
the area where N-2 is.
B-7, open fire
towards two o'clock.
P-5's team will
commence its barrage.
[COMM 1]
Gester team, contact lost!
[COMM 2] Enemy spotted
in district G-4-7!
[COMM 3] Kaczinski team
engaging. They were ambushed.
[COMM 1]
The enemy appears to be using
Sutherlands captured
from our own forces.
Exactly the same as Shinjuku.
Has there even been
any sign of zero yet?
N-2, continue towards
the upper-right.
R-4, fire.
N-1, take the man on the left.
Right. P-3, Take out the bridge
and close down the route now.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Point 1-7 has fallen!
Halley team, contact lost!
[CORNELIA]
That's enough.
Order all troops to fall back.
Further damage and
casualties serve no point.
[FORMER OFFICER 1]
Fall back?!
[FORMER OFFICER 2]
With all due respect,
we can still fight them!
We can't fight them like this.
[DARLTON]
All forces,
fall back behind ghetto
perimeter at once!
Formation doesn't matter!
Fall back behind ghetto
perimeter at once!
[LELOUCH]
What, no stomach for it?
If I blend in with
the retreating units,
that'll put me right
next to Cornelia.
Have I cleared the
task at hand already?
[C.C.] You can't fight your
own blood, can you?
But regardless, that type
of person is dangerous.
I wonder which path he'll take.
[C.C.]
I understand.
Just who do you
think I am, anyway?
[SHIRLEY]
Hmm...
So, Lulu lived here before
this became Area 11, huh?
Was he a neighbor?
[SUZAKU]
Um... What about yourself.
Myself?
I guess we're a lot
alike in that respect.
Honestly, I didn't like
Lulu at the beginning
when I first met him.
He gave the impression
that he was flippant,
and that the only thing
he worked hard at
was avoiding hard work.
But back when we were freshmen,
I happened to see him come
upon a traffic accident.
A driver rear-ended another
car and was clearly at fault,
but he tried to blame it on the
elderly owners of the other car.
Nobody tried to help them.
And then...
[SHIRLEY] Lulu didn't do
it so that he could boast
to his buddies or
laugh about it later.
He did it with the same bored
expression he always wears.
That's when I wondered,
"What's up with this guy?
What goes on in his mind?
What does he wanna do?"
I really wanted to know, and in
the process of finding out...
You fell in love with him.
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[SHIRLEY]
Umm...
You think that's what
this is? Maybe you're right.
How dreamy it is to be in love.
Oh, how I wish.
[LELOUCH] Cornelia...
You're no match, you'll lose.
Zero is no match, I'll win.
[FORMER OFFICER 1]
Huh?
Of course.
That's why they call Princess
Cornelia the Goddess of Victory.
Shall we go then,
Guilford, my knight?
It is my pleasure to serve
and obey you, my lady.
[LELOUCH]
Even with my Geass,
the normal security
makes it too risky for me
to simply stroll in.
I guess I'll have to create an
opening as I did with Clovis.
[phone ringing]
[LELOUCH]
Hm? The student council room?
But I thought the
cat festival meeting
was scheduled for tomorrow.
[SHIRLEY] I know Kallen
said I had it all wrong,
but it seemed like
she was getting upset
in order to fool me.
Which is why, in this case,
it's best to simply
ask him directly.
On your behalf, I can ask
him how he feels about you.
What?! You'd really do that?!
Just relax, it'll be fine.
Are you nuts?! No way!
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
Oh, whatever...
Aw, c'mon, let me
handle this for you.
I'll be discrete.
I don't want your help, okay?!
It'll be fine!
[SHIRLEY yelps]
Uh! Sorry!
Uh, oh... Does
that hurt much?
[SUZAKU]
Greatly...
[LELOUCH]
You're desperate, Cornelia.
Using your royal guard
in such a manner...
This is Zero.
N-1 will re-engage
their IFF signal.
Operate as a Britannian unit.
[TERRORIST C]
Understood.
[LELOUCH]
As my decoy.
[DARLTON] One knightmare left
transmitting an IFF signal
within the city area.
[FORMER OFFICER 1]
Can't you contact it?!
[FORMER OFFICER 2]
Scramble a rescue team!
No, destroy it.
You can't!
He might be a captive
of the enemy!
[CORNELIA] I ordered
all troops to fall back.
I have no use for soldiers
who can't follow my orders.
[DARLTON]
You heard the princess.
[FORMER OFFICER 1]
But--!
[CORNELIA] Do your duty,
even if it costs your life.
My subordinates follow
that code without question.
At your command, Your Highness.
Hey! What're you guys doing?!
Can't you read the IFF
signal?! I'm on your side!
[TERRORIST B]
Dammit!
No confirmation?
Well then...
N-2, send signal, then fall
back to the hospital ruins.
R-1, R-2, hold your positions.
Fire only if attacked.
They've transmitted another
signal, which means one thing.
They've set an ambush!
Send in more Gloucesters
and surround them!
They're not following?
No, dammit!
R-1, R-2, abort the ambush
and fall back at once! Abort!
[COMM 1] Gloucesters have
arrived at indicated area.
[COMM 2]
No sign of enemy.
He anticipated my move.
It's possible we really are
dealing with Zero himself.
P-2! N-3! Circle around
behind the enemy!
What's wrong?! Come in!
P2! N3! Dammit!
B-1! B-5! Move in!
Like hell!
There's no way we can beat
Cornelia's royal guard!
That's a death
sentence! I'm out!
[TERRORIST A]
Hey! We surrender!
[MAN]
We won't resist!
[TERRORIST C]
Spare us!
[CORNELIA]
Kill them.
P-6, P-8, what's
happening?! Agh!
B-7! Circle around
and cover N-4!
[TERRORIST D]
This is B-7!
I gotta prime target here!
I'll take him out first!
No, hold your fire!
That's a decoy!
B-7! That's an order!
Whaddaya mean? I've got this
bastard right in my sights!
Fall back! They'll strike
from above! B-7, fall back!
[TERRORIST D yells]
Idiot.
B-8, this is Zero. I want
a status report, now.
[TERRORIST C]
Screw your status report! Agh!
B-8! Damn!
Anyone who's left, report
in from the P group now! Uh?
[WOMAN]
Mission complete.
All forces, take
formation number 4.
[LELOUCH]
Beaten as easily...
But that's not how the
game is supposed to go!
[CORNELIA] This didn't work out
the way it did in Shinjuku,
Zero.
So, are you still
masquerading as one of us?
We'll discover
who you are shortly.
[LELOUCH]
This...
This is what real
organization can do...
[CORNELIA] Attention,
all Knightmare pilots.
Open your hatches
and reveal your faces!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Cornelia!
[CORNELIA]
Hah!
I repeat!
All pilots open your hatches,
and show me your faces!
[LELOUCH]
What do I do?
If she gets me in a line-up...
Without my mask, my
identity will be exposed!
That mustn't happen!
Use my Geass? No, impossible.
It won't work unless
I look directly at them.
The enemy is protected
within Knightmares.
That leaves the infantry
and the other pilots.
Huh-uh, forget it. There
are too many of them.
How do I turn this around?
No... Would that work?
Show them I'm Zero,
then use the power?
But then the the Knightmares.
Maybe I can start shooting
and break out of here!
Impossible.
Against Cornelia's royal guard,
that would be suicide!
[GUILFORD]
Open your hatch. It's your turn.
[gasps]
[GUILFORD] What's wrong?
Hurry up and open your hatch!
[LELOUCH] Well... my hatch
was damaged earlier in battle.
[GUILFORD] I see.
Then we'll open it for you.
[LELOUCH]
Uh!
[GUILFORD]
Turn around.
Well? Come on!
Yes, understood.
At once, sir.
[SOLDIER 1]
Zero's been sighted!
[LELOUCH]
Uh!
[GUILFORD]
Hm?
Ah-ha! I was right. Zero has
a flair for the dramatic.
No way!
[GUILFORD]
Capture him!
Platoons three and
five, stand ready!
[COMM 2] Image detected!
Target confirmed!
Twelfth tactical special
mobile company...
I'll just have to play along!
[SOLDIER 1] Surround the
building! Head around back!
[SOLDIER 2]
Sharpshooters, open fire!
[SOLDIER 1]
He fell!
Your Highness, how do
you want us to proceed now?
[CORNELIA]
Hm. Any likelihood it's a trap?
There's always that possibility,
especially since we don't know
anything about this person,
aside from the fact
that he seems
as prideful as you
anticipated, Viceroy.
Then there's no
point in chasing him.
[DARLTON]
Correct.
If he intentionally revealed
himself directly to his enemy,
he must already have an escape
route already in place.
[CORNELIA]
So self-preservation trumps all?
[LELOUCH]
That's how Cornelia is.
She's nothing at
all like Clovis.
Why did you rescue me?
[C.C.]
I told you already.
I can't have you dying.
[LELOUCH] I wouldn't have lost
if the conditions were equal!
You sore loser.
If you're really that good,
you should be able to set up
conditions the way you want.
That's what I'll do,
then. I'll set them up.
[LELOUCH] I'll raise an army
that can't lose to Britannia.
A people! A nation!
[LELOUCH] Where and
how can I find troops?
Who will serve in my army?
If only I could ask
Suzaku to join me...
No, that ship has sailed.
He's a Britannian soldier now.
Even if he doesn't enter into
the fray, he's still my enemy.
Well then, I'll
just have to choose.