[CC] Lelouch, a young
outcast prince of Brittania,
possesses two great powers:
One of them is Geass.
The absolute ability
to compel any person
to do whatever he commands.
The other is the Black Knights.
His military force assembled
with the intent of
destroying the Brittanian Empire
ruled by his father.
Veiling his true
identity behind a mask,
and the code name "Zero,"
Lelouch has made his move
to avenge his mother's murder
and to create a world in which
his younger sister, Nunnally,
can find happiness.
What will the be the final
outcome of these actions?
At this point...
no one can predict.
[REPORTER 1] ...clearing the
last of the debris from around
the Lake Kawaguchi
Convention Center Hotel.
[REPORTER 2]
It's been two weeks
since Zero unveiled
his Black Knights,
but there's still little insight
into the man behind the mask.
[REPORTER 1] They weren't able
to track his escape route?
[REPORTER 2]
They let the hostages go
and somehow made it
to the other shore.
[crashing]
[KALLEN gasps]
[MAID whimpers]
[MAID]
Unh! Kallen--I mean Miss.
Forgive me. I didn't
wish to wake you...
Again?
I'm sorry, it was the step
ladder this time, it broke...
Well, just get it cleaned up!
And be quick about it,
I have to leave for school.
Mistress...
You've been attending school
quite a bit lately.
Making any friends there?
I don't see how that's
any of your business!
Just go, will you...?
[OILY MERCHANT]
I know it's for welfare,
but why waste it on the Elevens?
[OILY POLITICIAN] That's why I'm
selling it to you, my friend.
The Eleven population could
use a little thinning out,
if you ask me...
[OILY MERCHANT]
Your payment'll be transferred
to your wife's account.
[OILY POLITICIAN]
Princess Cornelia is a soldier.
This sort of thing doesn't
interest her all that much.
--[BOTH gasp, whimper]
--[gunfire]
Hit the lights!
Turn 'em on!
[OILY MERCHANT whimpers]
[gasps]
You're-- You're the--!
[KALLEN]
The Black Knights!
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[STUDENTS laughing]
[SHIRLEY] That's not like you,
dozing off in class like that!
Well... I, uh...
[RIVALZ] You could learn
a thing or two from Lelouch.
He's an expert at
sleeping in class.
[KALLEN] Huh? He's not
sleeping now, is he?
[RIVALZ] I dunno what he's
up to, night after night,
but he sleeps through about
half of 'em these days.
[CORNELIA]
The E.U.'s starting an offensive
along the El Alamein front.
We can't go on dragging
our feet around here.
I want to solidify
domestic affairs.
It's high time Area 11 was
made a satellite nation.
For that to happen, we need to
stamp out terrorism, of course.
But another major problem is
the rampant abuse of "Refrain"
amongst the Elevens.
Productivity is plummeting.
It's coming in on the Chinese
Frederation's Kyushu route.
We have to put an end to it.
[EUPHEMIA]
Yes. But be careful.
[CORNELIA]
You as well.
I don't want you
leaving the settlement.
Cornelia...
What about the Black
Knights and Zero?
I'll let them roam
free a bit longer.
I owe them that
for saving your life.
However, upon my return...
Once I've cleaned up this area,
I'm entrusting it to you.
Try to stay out of harm's
way from now on.
All right, Euphie?
[ZERO]
Because Clovis was an offspring
of the Britannian emperor.
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
[ZERO]
That reminds me...
You're one of his children,
too, aren't you?
But I suppose for now...
[EUPHEMIA] When he spoke
to me that night...
...what was he alluding to?
Suzaku... What would
you make of all this?
About what Zero is doing...
And of me.
[yawns]
Man, this double life
sure is a killer...
[MILLY]
C'mon, Suzaku, hold him down!
[LELOUCH]
Dammit, Suzaku, cut it out!
Stop it! I'm not kidding!
[SUZAKU] Sorry, Lelouch,
but it's the president's orders.
[LELOUCH] Yeah, like you're not
enjoying this at all?!
[SHIRLEY]
Will you hold still?
[MILLY]
Huh? Good meowning!
Good... morning, I guess...
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
[KALLEN]
What is all this?
Whaddya mean,
didn't we tell you?
It's our welcome
party for Arthur.
Sounds like fun...
Well, classes are postponed,
we might as well have
some fun, right?
[SHIRLEY]
I set some stuff aside for you.
Over here!
To make up for all my
getting so upset before.
Take your pick!
[KALLEN]
What? For me?
She doesn't need a costume.
Wha...?
You're already wearin'
a mask, right?
You really are a riot,
you know that?
You oughta be on television.
What do you think,
Miss TV Star?
[SUZAKU] Oh, I thought
she meant Lelouch.
Would you quit
joking about that?
The whole thing's a
huge pain in the butt!
We've been hounded with
questions day and night!
Even in the bath!
[MILLY] We haven't been able to
leave school grounds in a week.
Not that I don't
feel for you,
but I don't see why
we can't leave either!
[MILLY] Hmm, that's
the price of friendship!
The Romance of
the Three Kingdoms.
"It matters not that
we were born apart,
upon this day we die as one."
Is that you're idea
of a love quote?
If I go down, then we all do.
That's a little dark.
Right, Suzaku? Huh?
I'm glad...
[RIVALZ gasps]
...that we could all
be together again...
Ya know, like this...
[sighs]
[RIVALZ]
Come onnn...
Hey! We're s'posed to
be unwinding in here!
[GROUP laughs]
That's what's so refreshing
about Suzaku though!
Yeah.
Though once in a while, you just
want him to get a clue, ya know?
Oh. Sowwy 'bowt dat.
Ah you love it, Putty-Tat.
[GROUP laughs]
[KALLEN] It's so funny to think
I helped save their lives...
Ever since we made our big
splash at the hoteljacking,
the Black Knights have
taken the world by storm.
We've become a friend
to the weak,
just as Zero
proclaimed we would.
Terrorists who involve
civilians, overbearing military,
criminal sydicates, corrupt
politicians and profitiers...
If the law would not punish
them, then we would.
In the blink of an eye,
we'd become heroes.
Support for us has swelled,
and we've even gotten our hands
on some Knightmares again.
Of course, no one could
show that in public...
...because...
[LITTLE BOY laughing]
[MOTHER] Stop pretending
you're a Black Knight!
[LITTLE BOY]
But why?!
You musn't ever say anything
against Britannia!
We're Elevens,
have you forgotten that?!
[KALLEN]
...because our leader, Zero,
had killed Prince Clovis.
There are many in our ranks who
wish to know his true identity,
myself included.
But if we push too hard, I
suspect that he would vanish...
And without him...
...I'm fairly certain
we'd be finished.
Hey there, pal.
Haven't seen ya much lately.
[LELOUCH]
Really?
Yeah, really.
Are you all right, young lady?
[NINA sighs]
[URABE]
Why would the masses
flock around those
who saved Euphemia?
[SENBA] Even Kyoto has
said that they would send
the Black Knights
the Guren MK-II.
[ASAHINA]
To those would-be Robin Hoods?
[CHIBA] They're not
part of the resistance.
Killing Kusakabe
was proof of that.
The colonel killed
himself, didn't he?
Well, I hear they
didn't try to stop him.
In any case, Lt. Colonel Tohdoh,
we can't let this stand.
[MAID]
Mistress Kallen!
[KALLEN]
Madame President?
I just dropped by to
give you something.
[KALLEN]
Huh...?
Where would you like
me to show her to?
The parlor perhaps? Or maybe--
We'll be in my room.
[MAID]
As you wish.
[KALLEN'S STEPMOTHER]
Oh. I heard you had
a friend down here.
I was sure it would be a boy.
Out all night
and missing school,
not to mention all your
visits to the ghetto...
You're lucky your father's
back in the homeland.
No fighting
one's blood, is there?
[MAID whimpers]
You're the one who's enjoying
Dad not being around here.
Aren't you?!
[KALLEN'S STEPMOTHER growls]
[crashing sound]
[MAID] Oh, dear...
What have I done...?
[KALLEN'S STEPMOTHER]
What's wrong with you?!
Forgive me, milady.
Forgive me...
[KALLEN'S STEPMOTHER]
Can't you do anything right?
Besides selling
your body, that is...
[MILLY] Quite the complicated
home life you have, isn't it?
[KALLEN] So what was it
you wantd to give me?
[MILLY] Grandfather
asked me to pass this on.
[KALLEN]
You mean the principal?
[MILLY] Your transcripts
since middle school.
[KALLEN gasps]
[MILLY] I thought I'd
better give them to you
off of school grounds.
So my secret's out then.
Isn't it?
That I'm actually an Eleven
and Brittanian half-breed.
That was my stepmother
down there.
My real mother was
that clod of a maid
who knocked over the vase.
And your father...
Is he the head of
the Stadtfeld family?
My mother is such a fool...
In the end,
she wound up a servant.
She doesn't have
any real skills,
and no matter who's
ridiculing her,
all she can do is laugh
like it's nothing.
She didn't have to choose to
stay in this house, ya know?
She just clinging to some
old lover who's jilted her...
You really hate your
mother, don't you?
I just find her depressing...
[MILLY] Wow, this is
getting a little heavy.
Imagine, the wife,
and the daughter,
and the "other woman,"
all living together.
[KALLEN]
Ah, it could be worse.
Three square meals
and a roof, right?
I mean, it's not unbearable...
Most of the time, anyway...
That's good.
Still... some things in life
we can bear on our own, but...
when you add 'em all up,
they eventually break you.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't lie, I'm always
hungry for secrets.
But I'd never talk about this.
[KALLEN'S REAL MOTHER whimpers]
[LELOUCH]
I can't believe you teared up...
It's so embarrassing..
[SUZAKU]
It's called "honesty."
[SUZAKU yelps]
[LELOUCH]
Well...
Good thing the Black Nights
were there to save 'em.
That's all I can say.
If they wanted
to catch criminals,
they could've joined
the police force, ya know?
Why don't they, I wonder...
[ARTHUR meows]
They probably don't think
the cops are up to the job...
I tend to agree...
The police may not be
that effective right now,
but they could evoke
change from within!
[LELOUCH]
Yeah, and in the process
get all tangled up in
red tape and bureaucracy.
If they had done everything in
their power to change things,
that might hold water!
As long as they don't,
then all of it's just
self-righteous posturing!
Self-righteous?
[SUZAKU] And what constitutes
"evil" in their eyes?
What standards are they using?
It's noting but self-satisfying
gratification.
[door slides open]
[SHIRLEY]
Oh? It's just you two?
Anyway.
I guess I've gotta go back
to the base pretty soon.
See you around, Shirley.
[SHIRLEY]
Uh, ah...
See ya later!
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
So, Lulu!
I was, um...
I was thinking,
if you had some time,
You and I--
"Back" to base, now that was an
interesting choice of words...
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Go back...
Implying that's where
he thinks he belongs.
[KALLEN]
Refrain?
[OHGI]
It's a psychotropic.
Makes ya think you've
gone back to the past.
[KALLEN] Must be all
the rage here in Japan...
[OHGI]
Yeah, well...
Who doesn't long for the days
before the occupation, right?
[grunts]
[OHGI] This stuff
was specifically targeted
at the Japanese.
We can't very well ignore it.
Soon as the Burais
are stocked, we move.
[KALLEN]
Supplies keep rolling in.
And I hear lots of people
are ready to join us...
Black Knights
sure are popular, huh?
[OHGI] Well, we are the
heroic Knights for Justice.
I'll call ya when
the ammo gets here.
[phone beeps]
[PUNK A]
C'mon, Eleven! Say something!
[PUNK B]
You are sorry, aren'tcha?!
[PUNK C]
Bowin' your heads
is what you Elevens
do best, right?!
Eleven...
[PUNK D] Eating bad food really
makes us want to off somebody!
[KALLEN]
Lelouch!
No, there're five of them.
You wouldn't stand
a chance at all.
So you think I should
just ignore it?!
Go on... take a good
look at that Eleven.
[PUNK A] C'mon, what's the
matter?! Aren'tcha gonna cry?
[VENDOR groans]
[PUNK A] C'mon, buddy!
Just say you're sorry!
[LELOUCH] If we intervene
and help him win,
he wouldn't be able to
sell a thing tomorrow.
It was his choice to become
a Britanninan slave.
That's just the price you pay
for working in the settlement.
Well even so--
[PUNK B]
You got a problem over there?
Not feelin' sorry for
this Eleven, are ya?
Nah, they feel the same
way we do, don'tcha guys?
Not quite.
[LELOUCH] But you're tired of
beating up Elevens now...
...aren't you?
Yeeah, this is boring.
You guys wanna hit the arcade?
[PUNK C]
I got no cash!
[KALLEN gasps]
Well, they got bored
pretty quick, huh?
[KALLEN]
Oh...
[VENDOR whimpers]
[KALLEN]
Hey, are you all right?
[VENDOR]
Huh...?
A Britannian student!
Wh-What can I get for you?
How about a nice
California hotdog, miss?
Ah! I-Is this your boyfriend?!
I can get him something, too!
I have ice cream, if you like!
[LELOUCH]
In some ways,
Area 11 is better off now than
the old Japan ever was...
Being made a colony of
the empire has stablized
its military and economic
position in the world.
Elevens can even attain
full citizenship
through the legal process.
It's easy to become
an honrary Britannian
Just a question
of pride really.
Though, I can certainly
understand why they'd resist...
--[KALLEN] And?
--[LELOUCH] Hmm?
[KALLEN]
Knowing all that,
what does Lelouch Lamperouge
think about it all?
What do you wanna do?
[LELOUCH]
Nothing.
You know, you've
got a lot of brains
but you don't seem to be
doing much with them.
It's all Shirley talks about.
Saying how intelligent you are,
but how you barely
ever apply yourself.
That's why I don't do anything.
That Eleven we saw
back there could tell you.
He can lead a better life,
as long as he bows
his head to Britannina.
[KALLEN gasps]
[KALLEN grunts]
[LELOUCH groans]
You must think you're
pretty cool, huh?!
Just playing the critic
and judging the world
from the sidelines?!
[growls]
Guess I was a fool to expect
anything more from you.
You know, I really thought you
were a better man than this!
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
[KALLEN'S REAL MOTHER whimpers]
[VILETTA]
So, about this Orange thing...
--[JEREMIAH grunts]
--Sorry to bring it up.
Is this whole thing true,
though?
That you can't remember anything
about when Private Suzaku
Kururugi was taken?
I don't expect you
to believe me.
No, it's just that...
During the whole
Shinjuku incident,
I suffered some sort of
memory lapse also.
You did?
By the time I
regained my senses,
my Sutherland had been stolen.
But right before that
entire gap in my memory,
I remember running into
some high school kid.
So what you think
it was that student?
I can't remember his face,
but there may still be a way
to get to the bottom of this.
[TAMAKI]
What the hell is Zero thinking?
After all his talk about
bringing down Britannia,
he's just got us running around
helping the police...
Still feels pretty good to have
the will of the people
behind us though.
[SUGIYAMA] Yeah, he's right.
We're totally heroes on the net.
[TAMAKI scoffs]
Are we in the right?
I don't know anymore...
Kallen...
[YOSHIDA]
There's the signal from Zero!
I can't believe
he got in there.
How many tricks does this guy
have up his sleeve anyway?
[SMUGGLER A] Is the
shipment for Nagoya ready?
[SMUGGLER B] Nice 'n safe
here in the settlement, huh?
[gunshots,
DRUG TRAFFICKERS yelling]
The Black Knights have arrived!
[SMUGGLER C]
Intruders!
A Knightmare!
[SMUGGLER B]
Screw this!
These Knightmares
really are amazing.
Each one is an army unto itself!
[gasps]
[ADDICTS chatter]
[MALE ADDICT 1]
Japan! Japan! Japan!
[FEMALE ADDICT 1] That's right!
I'm getting married next month!
[MALE ADDICT 2]
I've been promoted.
I'm going to the Paris office!
[FEMALE ADDICT 2] You'll see
the fireworks with me, right?
[MALE ADDICT 3]
Leave it to us!
Japan is on the vanguard
of technology!
Refrain...
I'm studying abroad!
I can't believe I got in!
[whimpers]
[MILLY] When you add 'em all up,
they eventually break you.
That's right.
Which is why I'm here!
[KALLEN'S REAL MOTHER] Careful!
It's dangerous to run like that!
[gasps]
[KALLEN]
Mother?!
[KALLEN'S REAL MOTHER gasps]
[gasps]
Really, Naoto!
Please, I need you to keep
an eye on your little sister.
My god how weak a woman
are you, Mother?
First you give in to Britannia,
then to a man, and now this...!
My brother is gone forever!
Let him go!
--[grunts]
--[gunfire]
[KALLEN gasps]
The Knightpolice?!
Isn't that a police unit?
They're in on this deal? Tamaki!
Don't look at me!
When I checked it out, there
weren't any cops involved!
[ZERO]
Corrupted filth!
[growls]
[KALLEN]
You're in the way!
Dammit! I don't need you!
I don't want you!
[grunts]
Kallen... Naoto...
[KALLEN screams]
[LELOUCH]
It won't work on a Knightmare!
Go on... run!
Get moving, you idiot!
I'm here for you.
[gasps]
I'm here for you, Kallen...
I'm here, as I always have been.
[gasps]
Then that's--
That's why you stayed
in his house?!
You stayed there for me...?
You fool!
[yells]
Or maybe... I'm the fool.
[OHGI]
Kallen!
[KALLEN grunts]
[KALLEN'S REAL MOTHER]
I'm so happy for you.
You can finally become
a Britannian now, Kallen.
Nobody will ever be able
to hurt you now, darling.
And you're free to travel and
use the phone any time you want.
[LELOUCH]
So this... is her mother?
[CC] False tears bring pain
to those around you.
A false smile brings
pain to oneself.
[FEMALE ATTENDANT]
It's an aftereffect of refrain.
She's unable to talk much.
She'll recover eventually,
but it will take time.
Mother, your sentence...
You got twenty years.
But you wait!
I'm working to change
things when you get out,
I swear to you!
I'll make a world where you and
I can live a normal life again.
So, please... Mother...!
[KALLEN whimpers, gasps]
[KALLEN'S REAL MOTHER]
Hang in there...
Huh?
[KALLEN'S REAL MOTHER]
Hang in there, Kallen...
My little girl...
[gasps]
Don't you worry.
I will. I promise you!
[LELOUCH]
Memories of the past?
Those who indulge in them
are foolishly happy...
because they assume that
tomorrow is coming...
But really... what
guarantee is there of that?
If Kallen is struggling to
dispel such illusions...
I'll stand by her.
All we can do is live each day,
one moment at a time.