[NARRATOR]
The date was August 10
in the year 2010 of
the Imperial calendar.
The Holy Britannian Empire had
just declared war upon Japan.
Confronted by Britannia's
newest weapon,
the formidable Knightmare Frame,
Japan fell to its enemy
in less than a month.
The conquered
nation was stripped
of its freedom, rights,
culture, and dignity.
Finally, even its
name was taken away.
Eleven.
The name of Japan and its people
was replaced with a mere number.
[JERIMIAH] Why the hell are
we letting the Elevens go?!
What about the poison
gas they've stolen?!
[OFFICER] But it's by
order of Prince Clovis!
[JERIMIAH]
What about Bartley?!
Get the general
staff on the line!
[OFFICER]
They're not at their posts, sir.
[JERIMIAH]
Are you telling me
Prince Clovis is
alone on the con?!
I'm overjoyed, Lelouch.
They said you died when Japan
was brought into the fold.
What a blessing
to have you back.
We should depart for
the Homeland immediately.
[LELOUCH] So you can use
me as a tool of diplomacy?
It seems you've forgotten
why we were used
as tools in the first place.
That's right.
It was because my
mother was killed.
[LELOUCH] Mother held the
title of Knight of Honour,
but was a commoner by birth.
No doubt the other imperial
consorts held her in contempt.
[LELOUCH] Even though
you made it look like
the work of terrorists,
I'm no fool...
You people killed my mother!
[CLOVIS] It wasn't me!
I swear to you, it wasn't!
Then tell me
everything you know.
The truth cannot be hidden
from me any longer.
By whose hand was she slain?
My brother, second
prince Schneizel,
and second princess Cornelia,
they can tell you...
They were at the heart of this?
[LELOUCH] That's all that
you know, isn't it?
[gasps]
[CLOVIS yelps]
I swear it wasn't me!
I had... nothing to do with it!
I believe you.
However...
Please, you can't!
We may have different mothers,
but you and I are still blood!
[LELOUCH]
You can't change the world
without getting
your hands dirty...
[MILLY]
Wake up, Lelouch!
I know you were sleeping,
your hand stopped moving!
Well ya don't have ta
beat me up over it, do you?
Ahh, serves ya right
for ditchin' me like that.
That's right. What was
up with you yesterday?
Oh, well...
That's enough you guys.
Let's not get sidetracked here.
If we don't come up with a fix
for the club activities budget,
there won't be money left
for anything at all.
And if it comes to that point...
The Equestrian Club'll
be pissed!
We don't want 'em comin'
in here on horseback!
Rivalz, can't you be a more
serious student council member?
You know, it woulda
been nice of you
if you would've reminded us
about this mess a day ago.
I would have to say a day later,
then we would've given up.
Good idea, we can
still do that.
Guts!
[ALL groan]
Are you tryin' that
"guts" spell again?
Yup. I want you people to start
putting your all into this.
I really don't think that your
magic's gonna do a whole lot.
Actually, it's got me
going, Madame President!
[MILLY] Supple and willing,
that's what I like.
I train hard in
the gymnastics club!
That's not what
I was getting at.
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
You're a ten.
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
[MILLY] From what I've seen
in the girl's bathroom anyway.
You've been filling out in
all the right places, huh?
[RIVALZ chuckles]
Wh-What are you
talking about, you perv?
Jeez, our president's just a
dirty old man on the inside.
Sullying the meeting
with her filthy mind.
[NINA] Yeah, well,
that's Milly for you.
[RIVALZ chuckles]
[RIVALZ]
Look on the bright side,
we got the budget
balanced, didn't we?
[MALE STUDENT A]
They used poison gas?!
[ALL]
Huh?
[MALE STUDENT B]
Man, that's freaky!
Shinjuku's only 30
minutes from here!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Oh my god,
I saw smoke rising
over in Shinjuku!
It musta been the gas.
[MALE STUDENT C] Are they
saying anything else about it?
Shinjuku?
I heard about it in
real time from a friend.
That's why I called
you yesterday.
[MALE STUDENT D]
Hey!
Check out the footage
of those dead Elevens!
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Uh! Don't look at that!
[LELOUCH] This is strange...
Why would they cover it up?
[gunshot]
[LELOUCH]
Are they hiding Clovis's death
to fend off anarchy?
But if that's the case, when
they finally do announce it...
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
I guess that I'm not as
tough as I thought I was.
That ex-civil servant
is such a fool.
So, are you referring
to Bartley?
The killer has breached our
heaviest security twice already.
This perfunctory
inspection is a farce.
Margrave Jeremiah.
Now that Prince Clovis is out
of the way, we purebloods can--
Let me make that call.
We still need to
woo everyone over.
[LONG WAVY HAIR GIRL]
Kallen! It's been ages!
[PIXIE CUT GIRL]
Are you all right?!
[PONY TAIL GIRL] Sophie's been
worried sick all this time.
[PIG TAILS GIRL]
You're okay though, right?
Yeah. I just have to go
easy for a little while.
[LELOUCH]
Of course...
That's why she's so familiar...
Anyway, if I stay home any
longer, I'll never catch up.
What's up, buddy?
See something you like?
You've got a thing
for her, don'tcha?
[LELOUCH] Just thinking
this is a rare event.
She hasn't been here at school
since this whole term started.
[ALL giggling]
[RIVALZ]
Kallen Stadtfeld.
[RIVALZ] They say
she's sick or something.
And she barely showed up
school last year, either.
Still, her grades are
at the top of the class.
And she's a member of
the Stadtfeld family,
which means she's well-bred
and rolling in money!
Man, you sure know
how to pick 'em!
[LELOUCH]
It's not like that.
[RIVALZ]
Ah, ya don't hafta hide it.
A touch too sheltered,
though, if ya ask me.
[GIRLS screaming]
[PIG TAILS GIRL]
There's a bee! A bee!
[KALLEN]
Huh?
[LONG WAVY HAIR GIRL]
Oh my god, Kallen! Run!
[GIRLS screaming]
[LONG WAVY HAIR GIRL]
Hurry up and run!
[GIRLS screaming]
I don't get it.
Why's a bee after me?
I wonder if there's
a hive nearby.
God, I hate this!
I'm sick of acting
like a freaking invalid!
[KALLEN]
Crap! He saw me!
[LELOUCH]
There's no question it's her...
Can... can I help
you with something?
[LELOUCH]
I want answers.
[KALLEN]
Of course.
Were you the one piloting
the Glasgow in Shinjuku?
Yes.
Why terrorism?
Because I'm Japanese.
Though technically
I'm half Britannian.
[gasps] Half blood?
But why go so far?
[gasps]
Um... Did you want something?
No. I got what
I wanted here.
Oh wait. Just to be sure...
Don't tell anyone
about Shinjuku.
[KALLEN]
Uh?
What do you mean
"about Shinjuku"?
[gasps]
[KALLEN]
Why would you say that?
Go back to class.
As soon as I get an answer
to my question, I will!
[LELOUCH] It's not working?
What's going on here?
[SHIRLEY]
Hey, Lelou! Kallen!
You know it's time to
head over to the Chem. Lab!
You better get a move on!
Ah, crap, it's my turn
to set up for class!
[LELOUCH]
It didn't work? But...
[SAYOKO]
Well, what shall we do?
He may be late
again this evening.
I'll wait. He said that we'd
have dinner together tonight.
There now. This one's finished.
[NUNNALLY]
Uh?
A bird?
Yes. It's a crane.
Amazing. The Japanese
are so skillful!
Lady Nunnally?
Uh?
I'm sorry I'm so late.
Hi, Lelouche. Welcome home.
Yes, welcome home, my lord.
No place like it, Sayoko.
Right, Nunnally?
[BARTLEY]
As you know full well,
the project was
a complete failure.
Therefore, this research
division is being gutted.
--[RESEARCHER 1] Wha--?!
--[RESEARCHER 2] Yes, but--
[BARTLEY] I've set up
a place in Narita for you.
Move everything out there.
While we may have
no memory of it,
the fact is, the other
staff officers and I
left Prince Clovis on his own.
I'm gonna be called
out on the carpet
for this back at home.
When that happens...
If His Majesty learns
this experiment's...
...gone on without his
knowledge... I...
[RESEARCHER 2]
Understood, sir!
We'll start prepping,
immediately!
[NUNNALLY]
Miss Sayoko was just teaching me
about the art of origami.
Fold a piece of paper
the correct way
and you can make birds,
boats, almost anything!
Uh, easy there,
you don't have to tell me
everything all at once,
you know.
It's not like I'm
going anywhere.
Yeah, you're right. Thank you.
You're very welcome.
[NUNNALLY chuckles]
[NUNNALLY]
I'm so happy!
'Cause last night,
you scared me a little.
Did I? Sorry, I just have
a lot on my mind is all...
[NUNNALLY]
Hey.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
They say if you fold a
thousand of these cranes,
your wish'll come true.
So if there's anything at all
that you've been wishing for.
No. Not really.
What about you? Do you
wish for anything?
[NUNNALLY]
Hmm...
I wish the world
was a gentler place.
When the day finally comes
that you can see again,
I'm sure that it will be.
[NUNNALLY]
Really?
[LELOUCH]
I promise.
The truth is...
...there are very few paths
our future can take.
The Ashford family's
sheltering us for now.
But how long can that last?
If our identity is exposed,
even Rivalz, Shirley, and
the others will abandon us.
We'll end up political tools,
or a casualty of royal ambition.
I have to build a world
where Nunnally can at
least find happiness.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
Sayako taught me
this the other day.
It's called a Japanese promise.
♪ Cross my heart,
hope to die, ♪
♪ eat a thousand
needles if I lie. ♪
♪ Pinky promise song! ♪
[giggles]
Well, that's scary.
I may have to eat a
thousand needles someday!
That's right.
So I better not catch
you telling lies, okay?
Don't you worry.
I'll never lie, I swear.
[LELOUCH]
Not to you, anyway.
This is the only weapon I have.
And I don't even
know how to use it.
[MALE TEACHER]
Lelouch!
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
Class'll be starting
any minute, you know.
[LELOUCH]
Oh, yes, sir.
Um, sir?
What are the topics gonna be for
the essays on your next exam?
The Humiliation of Edinburgh,
the transfer of the Capital,
and north 'n south war topics.
[LELOUCH] So. I haven't
lost the power then.
[LELOUCH]
Sir?
[MALE TEACHER]
Hm?
What exactly are
the topics gonna be
for the essays
on your next exam?
Right, very funny. Maybe you
should try studying, huh?
Just apply yourself,
you'll do fine.
Yes, sir.
[LELOUCH]
As I suspected...
...I can only use it
on a person once.
[OHGI] So, how's campus
life treatin' ya?
[KALLEN]
Stifling.
I was stuck in history
class yesterday.
Look, maybe I should
just head back.
[OHGI] The army's on
a high alert right now.
Stay there and
let things cool off.
[KALLEN] But what about
the voice on the radio?
[OHGI] Can't go lookin'
for a voice. Besides...
...Naoto would be happy
to see ya back in school.
Forget about Shinjuku
for now. I'll be in touch.
[KALLEN] Shinjuku...
I guess he's right, but--
[gasps]
Don't tell anyone
about Shinjuku.
[KALLEN] No, it couldn't
have his been his voice.
[LELOUCH] The aristocracy
was highly educated.
With such an emphasis on
edification and training,
they produced a superior
breed of ruler.
And secondly, they possessed
heightened efficiency.
Since only a...
[KALLEN]
It... could be...
No. I can't remember
well enough to be sure...
Good. That will do.
With the enthronement
of Henry the 9th,
son of the great
Elizabeth the 1st,
the golden age of
the Tudor dynasty...
[LELOUCH] All I did was
simply mention Shinjuku...
But...
[KALLEN] If he knows who
I really am, then...
[LELOUCH]
At the first opportunity...
[KALLEN]
I need to take care of him.
[BARTLEY]
And the research center?
[SOLDIER 1] Transferred
to Narita last night.
[BARTLEY]
Right then.
I pray you forgive me,
Your Highness...
[PONY TAIL GIRL] Why don't we
all go for out for some tea?
[GIRL B]
Kallen, you should join us.
[GIRL A]
Yeah, tag along.
Hey, Lelou. You comin' along?
Sorry, maybe some other time.
[KALLEN]
Maybe I can.
Yeah, I thought so.
You've gotta go
straight home then, huh?
What do you have,
a curfew? Huh?
[GIRLS]
Hm?
What's up?
You think that you could spare a
minute? I need to talk to you.
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?!
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[KALLEN]
Sure.
I was wondering when
you were gonna ask.
Huh?!
[GIRLS squealing]
[JEREMIAH] I hope you can see
how determined we are now!
But... I've already told you!
[JEREMIAH]
That you don't remember?
Still clinging to that
ridiculous excuse?
Just ask the others!
They'll testify that--!
Ducking the blame?
You're pathetic!
You shant remain at his royal
Highness's side another minute!
[KALLEN] I didn't even
know this room existed.
[LELOUCH] It's the club house
for the student council.
They built it as a ballroom
for various special occasions.
And we won't be
disturbed inside here?
Yes, that's correct.
[SHIRLEY]
Here it is!
I found it! Look!
This is it, right?
Ah! What a relief you
found our lab data!
[RIVALZ]
Ugh, good.
My ass is killin' me...
Were you able to find it?
I finished up on my end,
shall we dig in?
Aww, wow!
Way to go, Milly!
[MILLY chuckles]
[MILLY]
You adore me, I know.
Um... what is all of this?
Lelouch, don't you know?
I thought that's why
you brought her.
We're inducting Kallen
into the student council.
It was my grandfather's
idea, actually.
The principal's?
He thought it best
with her poor health.
She'd have a harder time
with regular club activities.
Oh! I'm Milly, the
president of the council.
Pleasure to meet you.
Oh. Thank you, the
pleasure's all mine.
I'm Rivalz, the secretary!
If there's anything you need
help with, I'm your man!
Hi, I'm Shirley.
And I'm a member of
the swim club. Welcome.
Um. Hi there. My name's Nina.
[KALLEN] It's...
nice to meet all of you..
[NUNNALLY]
Shirley? I'm sorry, but...
...do you think you could set
these on the table for me?
Oh, sure, thanks, Nunna!
Nunnally, what're
you doing here?
This is Lelouch's sister.
I'm still in the
middle school group,
so I can't be on
the council yet.
That's all right, you're an
honorary member in our book.
[NINA]
Mh-hm.
Hello, there. It's a pleasure
to meet you, Kallen.
Thank you. You as well.
[RIVALZ] Right! Shall we kick
this off with a toast?
--[MILLY] Huh?
--Champagne??
Yeah, but we're on the
student council, we shouldn't!
Ah, c'mon, loosen
up, you guys!
No way! We're gonna
get in trouble!
What's going on?
Here, Nunnally.
Lelouch, heads up!
[SHIRLEY] You're not getting
away with this either, Lelou!
What just happened?
[MILLY]
We have clothes for her?
[SHIRLEY]
Sayoko's on it.
This is why I hate
Britannians...
[knocking]
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
It's Lelouch.
I brought you a
change of clothes.
[KALLEN] You can come in.
I've drawn the curtain already.
[LELOUCH]
Uh... sorry about all this.
I know they can be
a little over the top.
[KALLEN]
That's okay.
Nothin' wrong with cutting loose
every once in a while, ya know?
[LELOUCH] These are some of
my clothes, hope that's okay.
It's cool. Don't worry 'bout it.
That was fast. You went all
the way to the boy's dorm?
[LELOUCH]
Actually, I live here.
[KALLEN]
Uh?
It'd be pretty hard for my
sister to live off in the dorms.
The principal of the school
lets us stay here, as a favor.
I see.
[LELOUCH]
Anyway...
Hey, wait!
[KALLEN] Can you hand me
that pouch over there?
[LELOUCH]
Sure.
You really are a
livewire, aren't you?
Were you the one in Shinjuku?
What do you mean?
[KALLEN]
Don't play dumb!
You brought up Shinjuku
the other day. Why?
Why do you ask, is there
something wrong with Shinjuku?
Don't answer my question
with a question!
Yes or no. That's all
I wanna hear outta you.
[phone ringing]
[LELOUCH] If I don't answer
it, someone'll come.
That okay?
Hello? Ashford Academy
student council.
Uh. No, this is... oh...
It's for you.
He says he knows you.
Hello?
[LELOUCH'S VOICE]
Glad you're still alive... Q-1.
[gasps]
[KALLEN]
Was I wrong?
[LELOUCH'S VOICE]
Sixteen hundred hours,
the day after tomorrow.
The observation deck at
Tokyo Tower. Come alone.
Who are you?!
How did you arrange
that cease-fire order?!
Uh! Hey! Don't hang up!
[LELOUCH]
Did you say "cease-fire"?
Sounds like you keep
dangerous company.
Oh, uh... that was...
[LELOUCH]
Let me guess...
You're talkin' about
a game? Something online?
Uh, yeah! You got
me. 'Cause, ya know...
...I've been shut up
in my house so long...
That's what I was
warning you about,
when I told you not to
bring up Shinjuku before.
Seriously, some guys'll
try to show you footage
of what happened that day,
and it's pretty damn grim.
By the way... you know
I can see you, right?
[KALLEN gasps]
[KALLEN yelps]
[LELOUCH]
Um, I won't tell anyone! Later!
I was wrong...
[LELOUCH'S VOICE]
Glad you're still alive... Q-1.
[gasps]
[SAYOKO]
Huh?
[LELOUCH] The council doesn't
require much actual work,
I guess.
Beyond occasional paperwork,
we'll sometimes
plan school events.
[KALLEN] So, you mean,
like the Culture Festival?
[LELOUCH]
Yup, like that,
along with the Cross
Dresser's Ball,
the Absolute Silence Party,
and Swimsuit Day.
What's up with that?
Blame our president.
You'll be spending a lotta time
with her. Hope you're ready.
[NUNNALLY]
Lelouch, it's awful!
[LELOUCH]
What is?
Prince Clovis has
been found dead!
They're saying he was killed.
[BOTH gasp]
Prince Clovis has
been taken from us.
He fought for peace and justice
against all of the Elevens!
He died a martyr!
We must all bury our sorrow.
And carry on his will.
[NEWS ANCHOR]
We interrupt this broadcast
with breaking news.
The man suspected as the
murderer has been captured.
According to this report,
the suspect is an
honorary Britannian.
What the--?!
[NEWS ANCHOR]
Private Suzaku Kururugi.
A former Eleven and
Honorary Britannian.
I repeat, Suzaku Kururugi,
arrested for murder.
[LELOUCH] Shouldn't I
be happy at this news?
Suzaku is still alive!
But... why has he been
arrested in my place?
I have to save him...
I don't care what it takes!
If I have to step up
my plans... so be it!
For I have the power to do it!