[SOLDIER gasps] The capital
Pendragon's been obliterated?!
[SOLDIER 2]
Is it true?!
[SOLDIER 3] They say it
was a F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
[SOLDIER 4] The thing that
wiped out the Tokyo Settlement?
[SOLDIER 2]
An accident?
[SOLDIER 1] But I heard
the F.L.E.I.J.A.s they built
are all missing now.
[JEREMIAH]
Stop spreading wild rumors!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
It's imprudent to talk
as if the capital's
been destroyed, even as rumors!
[SAYOKO]
No, I'm afraid it's all true.
What?! You!
Please take me to
Lelouch. It's urgent.
[LELOUCH gasping]
[LELOUCH]
N-Nunnally...
It's you... You're alive!
Yes, thanks to our
brother, Schneizel.
[LELOUCH]
Schneizel...
Nunnally...
Do you understand what
Schneizel has done?
Yes. He attacked
the capitol, Pendragon
with a F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
If you know about
that, then why?!
[NUNNALLY]
Do you think that using
Geass on people is better?!
[grunts]
Both you and big
brother have been
lying to me from the very
beginning, haven't you?
You've kept the truth
from me all this time.
But now I know everything.
[NUNNALLY] Lelouch,
you were Zero all along,
weren't you?
[gasps]
[NUNNALLY]
Why?!
Tell me. Were you
doing it for my sake?
Because, if you
were that means--
[laughs] For your sake?
I see my little sister
is presumptuous as ever!
[gasps]
You think it's just
natural for people
to help you all the time
out of sympathy and pity?
It's so easy to criticize others
while you keep your
own hands unsullied.
You are the quintessence
of the privileged aristocrat
that I've rejected.
You... No...
I act for no one's sake!
It is for me, my sake,
that I take the world
into my hands!
If you choose to stand in my way
by allying yourself
with Schneizel,
I won't hesitate to
crush you without mercy!
And without regret.
[NUNNALLY]
Lelouch!
[NUNNALLY sighs]
Are you all right, Nunnally?
That must have been
very hard for you, Nunnally.
I thought showing him the
power of the F.L.E.I.J.A.
might convince him to surrender.
[NUNNALLY] Schneizel.
Are the people of Pendragon
really all right?
Are you sure they're safe?
[SCHNEIZEL]
You needn't worry.
We gave warning for them
to evacuate well in advance.
[gasps]
[SCHNEIZEL] Of course,
the damage to the city
was significant, but we
did everything we could
to minimize it.
But, now we'll have to use
the weapon on people,
on Lelouch and his followers...
If they stand in the
way of world peace,
we'll have no choice.
Schneizel, please...
Will you let me have
the F.L.E.I.J.A.
firing switch to hold onto?
[gasps]
I can't fight battles
or defend my country
or my people.
So, at the very least,
I want this sin to
be on my shoulders.
Schneizel, may I please
have a word with you?
Tch!
C.C., why didn't you
find out about Nunnally?!
I'm certainly not a god.
I can only read people
if they're connected
to the power of Geass.
Tch! Schneizel!
You knew but you kept the
truth from me all this time!
Just so you could play this
card at the right moment!
Still, the way that
you shuffled the deck
was more than artful. It was
remarkable and effective.
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch.
[grunts]
Our strategic
objective's unchanged.
[LELOUCH gasps]
We can't stop this just because
we found out that Nunnally
is still alive...
Or the Zero Requiem
will have no meaning.
[gasps]
Remember your promise!
[C.C.]
Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
I am his sword.
It's my job to rid
him of his enemies
and his own weakness.
And you, C.C., you
must be his shield.
[C.C.]
Huh?
[SUZAKU]
Your job is to protect him.
We do things as you like.
[SUZAKU] Lelouch is your
accomplice, isn't he?
[C.C.]
My accomplice? Huh.
[CECILE] The F.L.E.I.J.A.
they used on Pendragon
had ten times
the effective range
of the one used on
the Tokyo Settlement.
[gasping]
[CECILE] If they haven't
developed a new model, then...
[NINA]
They've removed the limiter?
Bingo.
By removing both
the effect range
and the detonation
time limiter...
Prince Schneizel, how could you?
Yes, what about it?
[gasps] You mean the people
of Pendragon were...!
[SCHNEIZEL]
I made them vanish.
It was better for
them than a life,
swearing loyalty to
Lelouch, wouldn't you say?
[CORNELIA]
They're our own people.
And you told Nunnally--
[SCHNEIZEL]
Lies are expedient.
There's no need to tell Nunnally
things that would get in
the way of her opposition
to Lelouch, is there?
She'll never know
the difference.
[CORNELIA]
You use everyone?
Even your own sister?
Cornelia, what is it
that people truly want?
Starvation and poverty?
Discrimination and corruption?
War and terrorism?
They want the problems that are
flooding the world
to go away forever.
People can't
understand each other
under these situations at all.
Your theories don't justify
butchering civilians.
[SCHNEIZEL] Even civilians
who have rejected war
depend on the police,
don't they?
Everyone knows, don't they?
That people are driven
by their own desires.
The lust that dwells
within the soul of man
cannot be denied.
So why win hearts and minds
or tout some shining ideology?
Why not bring peace to the
world with a system and power?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[SCHNEIZEL]
In ten days, Damocles will enter
the airspace of the
United States of China,
and then switch over to
a secondary acceleration.
After that, we're
scheduled to ascend
300 kilometers
above the surface.
From there, we will
hit every enemy nation
with F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
Are you insane?!
We only agreed to use
them against Lelouch!
This will destroy the world!
You're trying to control
people through fear!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Mankind's history is war.
Peace is an illusion.
To turn illusion into reality
is an arduous task.
It requires discipline.
[CORNELIA]
And you plan to discipline
the entire human race
all by yourself?!
Only a god could pull that off!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Then I shall become a god.
[gasps]
If that is what
it takes to bring
peace to the world.
You're deranged.
[DIETHARD]
Magnificent!
I knew I was right
to change sides
and support you!
Surpassing Zero's
chaos with a state
of perfect nothingness,
and a kaleidoscopic
transformation!
Prince Schneizel,
we've made contact
with the Black Knights.
They say if you plan
to kill Lelouch,
they're willing to
join you immediately.
Thank you, Kanon.
Those who've experienced
Lelouch's tyranny
first hand will
have no alternative
but to choose the
lesser of evils.
Is that why you
stayed back and let
Lelouch get away
with this until now?!
[SCHNEIZEL] It was a way
to minimize the damage.
But in the end,
if we have to sacrifice
one or two billion
lives to achieve
a state of permanent peace...
You're wrong!
Peace attained by
force is not peace!
[SCHNEIZEL]
This is so sad, Cornelia.
[SAYOKO]
Schneizel outmaneuvered us.
He had another escape
plane as a decoy
during the battle of Tokyo.
And so...
[JEREMIAH] The plane
destroyed by the F.L.E.I.J.A.
was the decoy.
That's right, and now
he's trying to use
Miss Nunnally to
control Master Lelouch.
You're Japanese, aren't you?
Why come to Master Lelouch
instead of the Black Knights?
Uh...
You're devoted to
chivalry as well,
aren't you?
Ah. Perhaps there's
some truth to that.
[gasps]
[C.C.]
I'm impressed.
You didn't drop your mask
in front of Nunnally.
[LELOUCH]
No matter what angle I use
to attack the problem,
the answer is always the same:
The conclusion I came
to then wasn't wrong.
[C.C.] Lelouch, haven't
you done enough?
You've handled this well.
[LELOUCH] You understand
why I'm doing this evil,
don't you? Besides, under
the rule of Democles,
people would become
lifeless puppets.
That's true, but Nunnally
is aboard Damocles.
Everything you've done
from the beginning
was for her.
I can't treat her
differently any longer.
So many people have
died since this began.
For their sakes, we have to
see it through to the end.
Don't we, C.C.?
[sighs]
[C.C.]
Yes. You are right, Lelouch.
[KALLEN] Are you sure you
want to join with us?
It means you'd be
fighting against Britannia.
[GINO]
Y'know, right now...
Huh?
[GINO] Right now, I think
I understand your feelings
just a bit.
Uh...
Uh, well, thanks, I guess.
[GINO]
I beg your pardon?
[XING-KE]
Pendragon was the capital
of the Holy Britannian Empire.
With its destruction,
their internal
government is paralyzed.
[TOHDOH] They're confronting
our Black Knight forces
in every part of the world
so they're pinned
down everywhere.
[XIANG-LIN]
In short, the only force
Lelouch can deploy against us
is the division he brought
to reoccupy Japan.
But the balance of power
can be tipped for
him at any time.
To minimize damage,
we cannot hesitate.
The time to confront him is now!
Since Schneizel has
now agreed to join us,
our forces are evenly
matched with the enemy.
Our intention is
not the approval
of the Damocles use
of F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
It's bringing unity to the world
is our first priority.
This battle...
[LELOUCH] This battle
is the ultimate test.
Control of the entire
world at stake!
If we defeat Schneizel
and the Black Knights,
then there will be no one
left to stand in our way!
This world shall be destroyed
and then recreated
by Lelouch, the one,
true emperor of Britannia!
Crush them!
Destroy Schneizel and the
sky fortress Damocles!
Crush them all!
We have nothing to fear!
My name is the
future of this world!
[MASKED SOLDIERS]
All hail Lelouch!
[SCHNEIZEL] Lelouch has
spread malice and turmoil
all across the globe.
As the enemy of peace,
he must be wiped out.
It is time for
the Black Knights,
and for us, to cast aside
the grudges of the past
and join forces!
The people of the
world are waiting
for our song of victory!
I pray that, for all
time, this shall be
the last battle in the
last war that mankind
will ever need to fight!
Oh, Lelouch...
I'll make both of
you into records
on my hard drive.
[KANON]
Are you sure Anya
will be all right in the battle?
I know you promised to restore
her memory, Your Highness, but--
[SCHNEIZEL]
We need every bit
of battle strength
we have. So...
[alarms beeping]
Oh? An open channel?
Official greetings, Schneizel.
[DIETHARD chuckles]
[SCHNEIZEL] Lelouch, if
you're going to surrender,
now is the time.
We have an arsenal
of F.L.E.I.J.A.s,
ready to launch.
F.L.E.I.J.A.s? I wonder
if you dare to use them.
Considering that I
have all the U.F.N.
representatives aboard
the Avalon with me.
He's hiding behind
the hostages he took!
I can't believe
he'd go this far!
So, Schneizel, these
people are from
all over the world.
They're not related to you.
[SCHNEIZEL]
You're right, they're not.
Their lives are a
small price to pay...
Schneizel, you can't attack!
I understand that
the U.F.N. members
have elected
acting representatives
to speak for them.
We're prepared for the worst,
and we know how dire this is.
But that doesn't mean
we're going to throw
their lives away on a gamble!
[LELOUCH laughs]
[SCHNEIZEL] Li Xing-ke,
aside from the Damocles,
our strike force consists
only of the Mordred.
If you're going to tie
our hands so we can't
use the F.L.E.I.J.A.s,
then I request that you
put me in charge of
all our united forces.
[XING-KE]
We're facing Lelouch!
[SCHNEIZEL] Exactly. I've
never lost to Lelouch. Ever.
And I know him far better than
anyone on this battlefield.
[XING-KE]
Understood.
Deploy the Shen Hu.
Transmit the command
structure to all forces!
Yes, sir!
Then, shall we let the
game play out, brother?
[SCHNEIZEL]
Indeed.
Kanon, it's just
as you predicted.
Yes. The Black Knights
are now yours
to command, your highness.
Heh. Transmit pattern
Sigma to all forces.
Enemy fleets are in motion,
deploying into a wide-field
aerial formation.
He's using conventional
forces. Good.
Stretch our left wing!
Assume Half-Moon
Spirit formation!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Their main wings
are undermanned.
Have Gino's unit advance.
Keep the enemy's left
wing from extending!
[GINO]
Yes, Your Highness!
Checking my move.
Reverse the direction
of our left wing!
[CECILE]
That'll break up our formation!
[LELOUCH]
Do it!
Gino, halt your advance, now!
[GINO]
But why?
We should strike while
they're in disarray.
[SCHNEIZEL]
It's a false opening.
I'm not buying it.
[LELOUCH]
Not falling for it, huh?
Switch our battle plan
to Ursa Major formation!
Sixth Unit, follow Anya and move
to the northeast,
elevate 40 degrees!
Bombardiers, prep
for anti-air combat!
Anya, stop there, climb
200 meters and stabilize!
[TAMAKI] What the hell?!
Nobody's fighting!
You're wrong.
Contests fought
between two masters
are decided instantly.
An invisible battle
is now raging
between the two of them.
We have to hurry.
They're going to attack
each other any moment now.
They're surrounding us!
Counter move!
Reinforce the front line
with Suzaku's Lancelot!
Hold at combat speed four!
And send out Ward's unit!
Ah-ha, you haven't
changed, Lelouch.
You'd rather attack
my front line
than defend your own flanks.
[SCHNEIZEL]
I now have a small window.
Xing-ke?
[XING-KE]
Heh. He's already incorporated
our skill levels.
The enemy's left wing
is breaking away!
Stand fast!
Live up to His
Majesty's trust in us!
If we can defeat Lelouch,
this will be over!
If we smash their line,
it'll be a free-for-all...!
They're punching through!
They're cutting us to pieces.
Should I have Suzaku fall back?
[LELOUCH] No, that's what
Schneizel wants us to do.
Draw in the battle line!
Fall back and regroup!
Their fleet is damaged
and falling back.
[XING-KE]
Don't lose the momentum!
Push forward!
[HOSTAGES yelping, gasping]
[XING-KE]
Guren, you're too far out!
Match pace with us and
we can surround them!
I understand, but...!
Don't rush!
If we beat their vanguard,
we'll isolate the Avalon!
The Dreadnought is destroyed!
They're breaking through!
So that's how it stands.
I don't wish to engage the Black
Knights as formidable enemies.
However, my side has motive.
[SOLDIER]
For His Majesty!
It's heartrending.
Seeing soldiers controlled
by the false power of Geass.
And so!
[SCHNEIZEL] This is the
moment. Smash both wings.
Bow-mounted hadron
scatter cannon, now set!
[XIANG-LIN]
Move the Seventh Squad
out of the firing angle!
[FUTABA]
Gefjun control synched.
[MINASE]
Ready to fire!
Target both enemy
wings. And fire!
[OHGI] Zero, with all
of us working together,
we can defeat you!
It seems that Lelouch badly
underestimated the fighting
skills of the Black Knights.
Well, Lelouch?
Right.
They've shown great skill,
forcing me to use this plan!
Dammit!
Energy chain reaction, below us!
What?!
Impossible! He
timed this to...?!
[TOHDOH] All forces!
Deploy radiant shields!
[TOHDOH growls]
Zero!
[OHGI] I was the one
who first acknowledged
his leadership and encouraged
the others to follow him.
So I'm responsible
for all of this.
But I don't want a new
life caught up in it.
I know this is a
selfish request,
but I want you stay
here on Horai Island.
Please.
[KALLEN]
Ohgi, please respond!
Minami! Rakshata!
It can't be...!
He used the Sakuradite
in the Fuji mines.
Yes he has.
Destroying his own
ground forces as well.
[XING-KE]
I was careless!
So, that was Lelouch's
tactical plan.
But how could he sacrifice
his own forces?!
[C.C.]
This has drastically depleted
the enemy's strength.
Which leaves Damocles...
...wide open.
In reality, it's you
who's been checked.
And you brought it on yourself.
Nunnally, targeting is complete.
Now that the Black Knights
have been smashed,
we must use the
F.L.E.I.J.A.'s power.
[NUNNALLY whimpers]
Yes.
[NUNNALLY]
With this act, I will wipe away
my brother's sins!
Incoming! It's a F.L.E.I.J.A.!
So, he's finally launched.
Special division three!
[MAN ON RADIO]
Yes, Your Majesty!
It's useless.
It can't be stopped;
the F.L.E.I.J.A.
went critical the
moment it was fired
from the Damocles.
[LELOUCH]
Avalon continue to fall back.
All units, charge
at the Damocles.
Force them to keep
launching the F.L.E.I.J.A.
warheads until their
arsenal is empty.
[TAMAKI]
Ohgi! Ohgi!
[KALLEN]
Ohgi, please!
[TAMAKI]
This is no time to play dead!
[OHGI] I-I don't believe it.
You two shielded us?
[laughs] We were only
able to protect
the bridge though, eh?
You're on your own now.
Hang in there. Let's go...!
[TAMAKI]
Kallen!
[KALLEN] Oh, great...
Who's the guy giving orders?
[LELOUCH] Tch. Now that
I've used the Fuji plan,
and considering the number
of the remaining F.L.E.I.J.A.
warheads, I'm at a
disadvantage of one move.
Meaning, I have to
depend on Nina now.
Can she do it?
I know she hates me.
Detests me for being
Zero, Euphy's murderer.
The enemy of her precious
Britannia which I now rule.
And yet, to defeat Schneizel...
I wonder... Do you really think
you can defeat me, Lelouch?
Because if you do, you're
at the end of your path.
A man who has not
mastered the use
of the mask can never prevail.
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku and I...
Together, there was
nothing we couldn't do.
That's what I thought.
But now, Schneizel has
proven an unrelenting foe.
The truth is, it's his
detachment, his lack of desire.
A man coldly focused,
who understands
Geass and possesses
the F.L.E.I.J.A.s. What
strategy does he pursue?
Is there any tactic
that can work
on a battlefield
where F.L.E.I.J.A.s
rain down from the sky?
I have one last gamble,
one final card to play.
And it lies within
Schneizel's own heart.