[NUNNALLY]
Is that you, Lelouch?
It's me, Nunnally.
[SUZAKU]
If your memory hasn't returned,
you won't know who she is.
Go on, Lelouch,
let's hear your answer!
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku, you've got me trapped.
[NUNNALLY] Um. This is
my brother, isn't it?
[LELOUCH] I can't do this!
I can't lie to Nunnally!
[LELOUCH]
I... I... Uh?
Rolo?
Good work. Keep him like that.
You'll have to hurry.
Don't forget the time limit.
I know. Nunally, listen to me.
Lelouch! It is you!
[LELOUCH]
For right now,
we have to act like
we're strangers.
[NUNNALLY gasps]
[LELOUCH] It's necessary!
Just follow my lead!
I'm going to come
for you. I swear it!
And so, until then ...
Until then,
I love you, Nunnally!
[gasps]
Uh, you're confusing
me with someone else.
That's right, I'm just a
student at the school here.
[SUZAKU] Lelouch, your memory
really hasn't come back?
[LELOUCH]
Yes. I beg your pardon.
[NUNNALLY]
Forgive me.
When I heard you was a
good friend of Suzaku's,
I guess I just jumped
to conclusions.
It's just I...
No, please, it's an honor for me
to speak with a royal princess.
[NUNNALLY gasps] Um, could you
please put Suzaku back on?
[LELOUCH]
Yes, Your Highness.
[SUZAKU]
Forgive me, Nunnally.
I didn't mean to cause
a misunderstanding.
[NUNNALLY]
No, it's all right.
He just seemed so similar
that it surprised me.
Well, um, I'll see you
when I get to Area 11.
[GUILFORD]
Don't underestimate the threat.
He may be at a disadvantage,
but, we're still
dealing with Zero!
You can be sure he has
some plan underway.
[UPSON]
Such a cowardly response.
And they call you the
"Spearhead of the Empire". Hmph.
Fortunately, Viceroy Nunnally
has me to protect her.
Your services won't be needed.
But, general, Zero is--
Dead, Lord Guilford!
[GUILFORD gasps]
[UPSON]
Zero was killed last year!
The Zero we face now
is just using his name!
Princess Cornelia
would regret seeing
your contemptable fear
for this cheap imposter?
Speaking of regret.
[UPSON grunts]
Earl Asplund.
[LLOYD]
Sorry we're late.
Adjusting Lancelot took longer
than we thought it would!
It's been quite
a while, Earl Asplund.
That's because I'm working
directly under
little Charlie now!
Are you referring
to His Majesty!
[CECILE gasps]
Please forgive him, sir!
Lloyd, please!
[LLOYD]
Hm? Did I say something wrong?
I see that you
haven't changed.
As for the item we discussed...
Yes, It comes to us
via Prince Schneizel.
It's rather nice, having a
second prince to call on.
You have my thanks.
[UPSON]
Unbelievable!
This prodigal
aristocrat is serving
as Lord Kururugi's guardian!
He'd better not
interfere with efforts
to educate the new viceroy.
[NUNNALLY]
Did Suzaku lie to me?
But, my own brother...
I don't understand.
Has something
happened between them?
[MALE NEWSCASTER]
The new viceroy is set to arrive
at Area 11 tomorrow
to take up her post.
The name and background
of the new viceroy
still has not been
released to the public.
The big question's the Chinese
Federation consulate, right?
You mean regarding Zero?
As there has been no
formal announcement,
some think Chief Consul Gao-Hai
may be acting on his own.
The consul general's
standing will depend
upon the balance of power...
[EUNUCH A] W-What about
the stand-off in Area 11?
[KAGUYA] Oh, I'm afraid
I don't know the details.
[EMPRESS] Can you tell
me anything about the
outside world? I've never gone
beyond the walls of this palace.
[EUNUCH A] That's because
this Forbidden City in the
Luoyang Capital is the very
center of the world, Empress.
[EMPRESS]
But...
I'm going to go outside
and see what's happening.
[EMPRESS]
Huh?
[KAGUYA] The truth is, I came
today to say goodbye to you.
Oh, no!
Not now, when I've finally
made a real friend.
I'm very sorry,
but you know my husband
is waiting for me.
[C.C.] The supplies
were successfully
received in Niigata.
[LELOUCH]
I see.
[C.C.] However, there's no way
for them into the consulate now.
[LELOUCH]
As expected.
Nunnally is going to
be the new viceroy.
Will you be able to fight her?
Your sister?
[LELOUCH]
Fight? Nunnally?
Is that some kind of joke?
Then you're just going
to leave her alone?
[LELOUCH]
Out of the question.
If nothing's done,
Nunnally will be used
as a political tool,
just like she was before!
[C.C.] A girl who can't
walk and can't see...
Do they plan to use her as
a pawn, then throw her away?
[LELOUCH growls]
I'm doing all this to keep that
from happening! That's why I
formed the Black Knights!
I became Zero for
Nunnally's sake!
I'm well aware
that your sister's
your entire reason for living.
However...
I am going to create a world
where Nunnally can live happily!
To do that, I will
obliterate Britannia!
You mentioned, V.V. Is he
in the Britannian homeland?
I don't know that
much about him.
However, I know that he's
your father's first ally:
Emperor Charles of Britannia's
chief confederate.
[LELOUCH]
Confederate?
[C.C.]
Long ago, they made a pact.
I shall slay the god!
Yes, that is our
binding contract.
[V.V.] Tell me, Charles,
why didn't you tell Nunnally
about Zero's true identity.
And about Geass.
[EMPEROR] It wasn't
necessary for her to know.
You know, Charles, you really
are still a child.
Perhaps I am, big brother.
Where's Viceroy Nunnally?
[SHIP ADJUTANT]
She's in the garden.
Even if she came
to the bridge...
[UPSON scoffs]
I guess there'd be no point
[SUZAKU]
The Black Knights?!
They're not here?!
[XING-KE]
Right.
We only just
confirmed it ourselves.
I'll give you all the
information I have.
That way, it should
be crystal clear
that my country has no hostile
intentions toward Britannia.
Did Zero go with them?!
[XING-KE]
It appears so.
They took their knightmares
with them and they vanished.
We're guessing they left
through an underground level.
[SUZAKU huffs]
To where?
[XING-KE]
No idea. That's all I have.
They wouldn't attack Nunnally?
We've been had.
Should we... strike back.
[UPSON]
The Black Knights!
[ZERO]
The objective of this operation
is the capture of
the new viceroy!
No matter what happens,
she absolutely
must not be harmed!
Keep her safe, is that clear!
[BLACK KNIGHTS]
Roger!
Tamaki, what are you doing?!
Amateurs!
Bringing land-based units
for an aerial mission-- Ah!
Surface flares will have
no effect on our defense.
Surround and attack now!
All right, General Tohdoh,
the rest is up to you.
Right. Good luck,
Deputy-Commander.
[UPSON]
Impossible...!
They're landing on top of us?!
[RADIO TECHNICIAN A]
Two more enemy Knightmares
have landed on our main wing!
[RADIO TECHNICIAN B]
They're on our escorts as well!
Send our aerial forces to--
[booming]
[LELOUCH]
You took the bait, commander.
I figured you'd concentrate
your air power on the smoke.
The obvious response.
Now we can focus
on the flagship.
All right! We're withdrawing!
[UPSON]
Deploy the remaining air ships.
Have the escort
ships fire as well!
[SHIP OFFICER A] But sir,
the enemy is targeting
our float units. We can't shoot
back because our shields are up!
Then how can we
defend this ship?!
[grunts]
If I'd known this was possible,
I'd have brought
Lord Guilford along!
It'll take an hour
for reinforcements
to reach us from the
Tokyo settlement!
[ORANGE VEST] What if a
Knightmare makes it inside?
[LAB COAT]
Then we crash.
Our job now is to
help the survivors--
[BOTH gasp]
What... is that?
[ZERO]
Die!
--[ORANGE VEST gasps]
--[LAB COAT gasps]
Ya.
Understood.
[LELOUCH] Nunnally,
I'm coming to save you.
Now, Samurai Leap over
Floating Boats attack!
[ASAHINA]
You can put your shields up,
but once we get inside,
your finished.
Looks like they're running
out of air strength too.
You'll end up a skinned rabbit.
Don't get cocky.
Right, right.
I'll stick to basics, but, huh?
Reinforcements from Tokyo?
So soon?
No, it looks like
their rear guard.
And, they have float units.
[KALLEN]
Knightmares!
[KALLEN gasps]
[KALLEN]
It can't be That machine is...
Now, Let's bring
down the curtain.
[CECILE] Output on
all units is normal.
Isn't mass production nice?
Well, I'm not so
sure about this.
Did Prince Scneizel
really approved the budget?
If he didn't, he'll notice
it pretty soon.
What?!
You didn't tell him
what you were doing?
[KALLEN]
I don't need to fly for this.
You have the right instincts,
but the wrong Knightmare.
[KALLEN huffs]
Sorry! I'm out.
Damn Guilford,
acting without orders!
But he saved us, my lord.
Yes, and he'll take all
of the credit for it!
[LELOUCH] All tasks at
hand have been cleared.
And now, the tide of
battle shall turn!
[LELOUCH gasps]
Nunnally...
Look! Zero's inside!
What are those guards doing?
Viceroy Nunnally, it's Zero!
[NUNNALLY gasps]
[SECURITY GUARD B]
I'm informing General Upson now.
[SECURITY GUARDS groan]
Their reunion is starting.
It must not be disturbed.
[LELOUCH gasps]
Nunnally...
[LELOUCH]
We're together again. At last.
You're, Zero, aren't you?
The terrorist.
Have you come to
kill me as well?
Like you killed
my brother Clovis
and my sister Euphie?
[NUNNALLY] Even so, will you
wait just a moment, please?
I think that what
you're doing is wrong!
[grunts]
It's a Harken!
Hit him now, Kouzuki!
[KALLEN]
Right!
[KALLEN grunts]
[gasps]
Okay, it's discipline time!
What a weird-looking
fighter plane.
Even so...!
[ASAHINA]
A Knightmare?!
[grunts]
I'm finished. Sorry.
[SHIP OFFICER B] That just
leaves four enemy units.
The Knights of
the Round as well!
I'll never bear this disgrace.
--[computer beeping]
-- Now what?!
[SHIP OFFICER C] Starboard
escort ship has lost control!
What?!
[SHIP-OFFICER C]
It's on a collision course!
[UPSON]
Turn the ship!
[SHIP ADJUTANT]
We'll never make it!
[SHIP OFFICER C]
We're going to crash!
[yells]
[GINO chuckles] The Mordred
always handles things
in its own unique way.
Anya, don't do
that again, okay?
We don't want to kill
the viceroy now, do we?
But I saved her.
Lloyd, how's the Lancelot?
[LLOYD] Ready and waiting
for you! Come and get it!
General! What are you
doing in that gun turret?
[UPSON] At this rate,
I'm going to be demoted!
I have to do something
to prove myself!
I'll kill the Black Knights!
[gasps]
[UPSON laughs]
You fool! You shot
your own engines!
[grunts]
[NUNNALLY] Right now, Zero is
standing in front of me.
Lelouch, give me
the courage I need.
[ZERO]
It's Britannia that is wrong.
The emperor believes
that might is always right.
Do you approve of that?
[NUNNALLY]
Well...
[ZERO] Viceroy Nunnally,
you're just being used.
You're saying
they sent a blind,
crippled girl to win
everyone's sympathy?
Then, you're wrong.
[ZERO]
Hm?
[NUNNALLY] I asked them to
send me. That's why I'm here.
[LELOUCH gasps]
Where's Zero?
[TOHDOH] We can't contact him
because of the ECCM effects.
I want to rendezvous
with Chiba and Kouzuki
and scout inside the ship.
[SENBA] But the
ship's going to crash.
Do you think you
have time for that?
It's very--
[TOHDOH]
Senba!
I don't like picking on those
who are weaker than me, but...
Never thought a
place like this...
[TOHDOH]
Senba!
[GUILFORD] Using land
units for an aerial attack?
That's not your kind
of tactic, Toudo.
[ZERO]
You requested it?
[NUNNALLY] I think with
a peaceful approach,
I can make the world
a more gentler place.
That's why I want to
carry out Euphie's plan
to create the Specially
Administrated Zone of Japan.
[ZERO]
You'd have that return?!
Zero, won't you please try
to help me to rebuild it?
[ZERO gasps]
[NUNNALLY]
People can start over! Please!
[SUZAKU] Zero's coming to steal
Nunnally away, but there's been
no word from the Office
of Secret Intelligence.
So, am I fighting
Zero or Lelouch?
Sir Kururugi, I'm confirming the
data now. The number two float
unit on Viceroy Nunnally's
Flagship has shut down.
The number 3 and 4 float
units are interlinked,
so a case theta has occured.
[LLOYD]
To sum that up,
we'll all be swimming
in the ocean soon.
Uh. Except for general Upson,
who's regrettably
didn't make it.
Right now, rescuing the
viceroy has top priority!
[CECILE] Initiating search
for her wheelchair beacon.
Starting E.C.M.
Signal noise cleanup.
Phase, preset. Sending the
layout of the ship's interior.
[SUZAKU]
Confirming Data link.
[CECILE]
Complete.
Transmit the viceroy's
location as soon as it's known.
[CECILE]
Channel M.B., roger!
Lancelot Conquista...
Now launch!
[SUZAKU]
Launching!
[KALLEN gasps]
Kallen, I have to save Nunnally.
Nothing else matters now.
I won't ask for your
forgiveness... any more.
Kouzuki, hide!
Get inside of the ship!
[KALLEN] I can't Not until
everyone's gotten away!
What the hell!
Kouzuki!
[CHIBA growls]
[CHIBA]
Pull the eject lever, Kouzuki!
No use! It isn't working!
[CHIBA] Defective equipment
at a time like this!
[grunts]
[ANYA]
Tag, you're dead.
[computer beeping]
[gasps]
I'm falling!
Forgive me, Guren...
Mother, Naoto...
[whimpers]
What a perfect position!
Wha--? Rakshata?
[RAKSHATA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I have the new Black Knight
glide wing pack for you.
You did review
the manual I sent?
[KALLEN]
Uh, sure. I'm good to go!
All right, let's try
it out then.
We'll give you the
basic guidance from here.
Please rescue Master Zero.
[KALLEN]
Uh, right!
[CREW MEMBER A]
Opening number 3 launch chamber.
[CREW MEMBER B]
Connection signal with
Guren Mk-II, confirmed.
Take to the skies,
my soaring glide wings!
Rotate!
[CREW MEMBER A]
Guidance signal, confirmed.
[CREW MEMBER B]
Contact angle, aligned.
[RAKSHATA]
Link up.
[KALLEN]
Linking up!
Fly!
Armor piercing artillery,
right arm unit!
[CREW MEMBER A] Right arm
unit decelerating for linkup.
Transmission neuron
0.5 to 0.8 M.M.P.
No obstacles detected.
Elastic muscles 1 through
5 are operating normally.
Activation of shock control,
confirmed. Linking up.
Kallen, please.
No matter how many
enemies are coming...!
[GUILFORD] Our unit
will go after Tohdoh!
[GINO] Right, and we'll
protect the viceroy.
Huh? In the sky?
The Black Knights have
a float system, too?
Kouzuki! Save Zero!
I'm on it, sir!
Oh? You've gained wings and
a shield, huh? So what!
If this Guren doesn't work
perfectly, then I'm finished.
Well, we don't have
much choice, try shooting it.
[KALLEN]
You've got a point, there!
[GUILFORD gasps]
From long range?!
[GUILFORD grunts]
I can do it! With this Guren
Flight-Enabled Version!
Nice one.
[GINO]
Suzaku, get to the viceroy!
[SUZAKU]
Don't let your guard down!
That's the pilot who
defeated Lord Jeremiah!
[GINO]
The one who beat Orange boy?
Come on!
Well, look at that.
As good as the
Knights of the Round?
We'll see, right now.
Don't underestimate the Guren!
[ANYA grunts]
Dirty shoes.
I'll take care of
you guys later.
Gad!
It can fire wide-range, too?!
What's its total energy?!
[CECILE]
The same amount, but scattered.
With the internal
damage it caused,
those units won't be able
to function for a while.
So, what's with that knightmare?
Uh-uhh. It's all the pilot.
I shouldn't have held
back on my attack.
[SUZAKU]
Kallen, Why would you come back
under these conditions?
Is it that Zero's on
the ship already?!
MOVE IT!
[RAKSHATA]
Have a taste of the Gefjun Net!
We have a countermeasure
for this!
[KALLEN] You're still
stuck where you are!
No way!
It can't be more powerful than
and advanced Yggdrasil Drive!
[CECILE]
Suzaku!
We've located the viceroy!
She's in the garden space to
the rear of the main bridge!
But hurry!
Now there's only 47 seconds
till the ship crashes!
[SUZAKU]
I promise, I'll save her!
Damn!
[LLOYD yells]
[C.C.]
Kallen! Forget about Suzaku!
[KAGUYA]
Save Master Zero!
I understand, but where?!
[SUZAKU]
Tsk! There's no time left.
I'll have to use the
Core Luminous Cone.
Go!
[LELOUCH]
What do I do?
I can't reveal Zero's
identity to her,
but I can't take her
by force either.
I can see now that
would traumatize her!
[ZERO gasps]
[ZERO]
Suzaku!
[NUNNALLY gasps]
[ZERO]
Escape with me!
Nunnally!
Suzaku!
[ZERO gasps]
[LELOUCH] No! Not after he
sold me out to the emperor!
Suzaku! Down here!
[ZERO grunts]
[SUZAKU]
Were you frightened?
Forgive me! It's all right now!
[LELOUCH gasps]
Nunnally with Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
Zero! Not this time!
[ZERO]
Nunnally!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] Eight years ago,
because our mother was murdered,
because we were
abandoned by Britannia,
protecting Nunnally
became everything to me.
Cleaning the house,
making our dinner everything.
But now! I'm a fool!
Nunnally has
dreams of her own.
She has chosen a
path for herself.
It's so obvious. So simple.
[LELOUCH gasps]
What should I do?