[groans]
[SUZAKU]
Where's the Lancelot?
Zero!
It's no use.
I can't remember anything.
[LELOUCH]
Where am I?
[SUZAKU]
Just as I thought.
This is another island.
[LELOUCH]
The vegetation and climate
are the same
as Shikine Island.
We can't be that far from it.
[SUZAKU] There's no way to
contact anyone without an incom.
But what's more important
right now is to find
a source of drinkable
water and shelter.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Kallen? It can't be.
Excuse me!
Suzaku?
A Black Knight uniform?!
You mean that you're a--
[KALLEN growls]
I don't believe it.
It's really you?
[KALLEN growls]
[KALLEN gasps]
[KALLEN yells]
Kallen!
Kallen Stadtfeld,
I don't believe it! You're--
[KALLEN]
Don't call me by that name!
Kallen Kouzuki's my real name!
I'm Japanese!
You're kidding,
then you really are...
[KALLEN]
Yes!
I'm a Black Knight, got it?!
I'm not going to
hide that anymore!
Well then, Kallen Kouzuki,
I'm placing you under arrest,
for conspiracy and rebellion
against Britannia!
[LELOUCH]
Tsk!
Contacting Ohgi and the others
is going to be a chore.
Although...
I suppose I could pass myself
off as an ordinary person
and ask the Britannian
forces to rescue me.
Huh?
[SUZAKU]
I see.
Then you don't know
what happened, either.
When you came to, you found
yourself on this island.
Is that right?
[KALLEN] So then you're
stranded here, too, huh?
Serves you right.
When my people get here,
you're the one
who'll be a prisoner!
[SUZAKU] You mean Zero
will come to save you?
Without a doubt.
Okay, before he does,
tell me one thing.
Tell me who he really is.
[KALLEN] Why don't you
find out for yourself?
[SUZAKU]
Oh, I see.
You don't know, either.
[KALLEN]
How did...?
I knew it.
[KALLEN]
You tricked me?
Isn't masking one's
identity a bigger fraud?
I'm curious,
why do you follow Zero?
[KALLEN] I dunno.
Figure it out for yourself.
[EUPHEMIA]
Lelouch.
Lelouch, it's you, isn't it?
I haven't told
anyone about you. I swear!
Please... before you shoot...
Let me at least see your face.
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
Lelouch!
[COORDINATOR A]
Underground probe radar team,
move from section D
to section F.
[COORDINATOR B] Establish
a 5 second silent interval...
[FAYER]
Find her!
Whatever it takes,
find Princess Euphemia!
Why couldn't she behave the way
a sub-viceroy figurehead
is expected to?!
What a situation!
If Princess Cornelia
hears about this...
[LLOYD]
Oh, my!
Who would have imagined
a floating aircraft carrier?
You told me to gather data
before practical application.
Correct?
Because I'm extremely interested
in whatever you create.
I needed to see if
this could be made real.
And the hadron cannon?
We wanted to know
if the thing worked.
[SCHNEIZEL] I've been looking
forward to meeting you,
Ms. Cecile Croomy.
I am--
Prince Schneizel?!
Right here?!
You impudent little--!
How dare you look down upon
the second prince of the empire!
G-General Bartley!
[yells]
Nice one.
[CECILE groans]
[SCHNEIZEL]
You're not injured, I hope.
Yes, I am Prince
Schneizel el Britannia.
Please, give me your hand.
Yes...
Ugh! She's unworthy!
General, you're quite the
devoted subject, aren't you?
Primarily because
the prince is the one
who commuted my
sentence and saved me
from being chained up
deep beneath Temple Tower!
I wish you'd stop
thinking of me so formally.
You've been a great help
to me in this current matter,
as you were to
my brother Clovis.
It is I who
am grateful to you.
[BARTLEY]
M-My lord...!
Please, Bartley.
[SCHNEIZEL] Now, my lady Cecile,
if you'll excuse me.
Y-Your Highness!
Farewell.
You can wait for me
at the base, Cecile.
Huh? Where are you going?
[LLOYD]
Just a little errand.
While I'm doing that, I'll use
the Avalon to look for Suzaku.
It's hard to find
devicers like that young man,
especially after
yesterday's exploits!
[CECILE]
Please wait.
Were those orders yesterday
issued by the prince?
Silence!
You don't want to be in
contempt of royalty, do you?!
Those orders
were mine, Miss Cecile.
I also fired the hadron.
Even in a situation like that,
priorities mustn't be forgotten.
Besides, if something
anomalous happened,
we would have still
been able to rescue him.
That's what I gambled on.
He is, after all,
Suzaku Kururugi,
ace pilot of the Special Corps
and Euphy's knight.
Yes, my lord. I understand now.
And I sorely regret my rudeness.
I accept any
punishment you decree.
Nonsense.
It's my fault for not
protecting my subordinates.
Can you ever forgive me?
[LELOUCH]
When did you figure it out?
[EUPHEMIA]
Back during the hotel jacking.
[LELOUCH]
I see...
At that time, I said
too much without thinking.
[EUPHEMIA] Still, I wasn't
convinced until now.
[LELOUCH]
Hmph. I'm naïve as well.
Even so, why didn't you
discuss it with Cornelia?
I didn't because my
sister never listens to me.
Besides that...
I think things are
depressing enough as they are.
Nunnally? How is she?
[LELOUCH]
She's living with me.
But she's still
blind and crippled.
The hatred you
must feel for us...
I only want to
find out one thing.
Do you know anything
about the circumstance
in which my mother was murdered?
I'm sorry.
It seems my sister's
investigated it
extensively, though.
Cornelia thought
a lot of Lady Marianne
and really looked up to her.
[EUPHEMIA] May I ask you
something now?
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[EUPHEMIA]
Are you Zero?
Or... or are you...?
I'm Lelouch.
Yeah.
Right here and now, I'm Lelouch,
the brother that
you know, Euphy.
Oh, Lelouch...
[crying]
[stomach growling]
I believe feeling relieved
has made me hungry.
Are you sure
that this will work?
From the paw prints
and droppings,
I can tell that wild
animals use this path.
I plan to set up a trap
that dates back
to Medieval times!
[EUPHEMIA]
Oh...
Gotcha, haha!
Oh wow! You're not bad at that!
Do you wanna try it, too?
I tell ya what,
I'll let you loose if you
promise to help me find food.
Is that a deal?
Hmph.
You're not gonna
win me over, so why try?
What do you take me for?
[SUZAKU]
Man, you're stubborn!
You're not anything like
the way you are at school!
Even using... a lever...
Why don't you let me
help you with that?
Manual... labor isn't...
for a... royal princess.
Don't worry.
My method's perfect.
Well, I suppose...
I could go and search
for something, like fruit!
Okay?
Be careful, Euphy!
Right!
[SONAR OP]
Enemy battleship has passed us.
[TAMAKI]
You've gotta be kidding!
A battleship that
can hover in midair?
That's great!
We can't remain
in this area any longer.
The risk is too great.
We should pull out of here.
[OHGI]
Mmhmm.
Ohgi. I disagree.
We ought to at least stay put
and look for Zero.
He has a point.
But we can't send out a
search party in this situation.
Even though we're able to hide,
thanks to Rakshata,
there's no guarantee Zero
and Kallen are still alive.
One wrong step, and we
threaten the very existence
of our organization.
What do you mean?!
It's entirely
the other way around.
This entire organization
is built around Zero!
It's not a group
without members!
The way you speak, you sound
like a typical Britannian to me.
[DIETHARD]
All right, then, answer me this.
We have followers
of almost every ideology
under the sun gathered here.
Yet how is it that
the whole lot of them
can cooperate and work
together toward the same goal?
Because of the results we get?
Tell me, who is it
that gets us those results?
[TOHDOH] I'll be the first
to admit that he does!
But is he worth
the lives of everyone?
At times, the life
of a single man
is worth more than
those of a million.
I thought that would be
common sense to a soldier!
You dare say that here?!
Easy, guys.
[C.C.] Oh, all right,
then I'll tell you.
He's very much alive.
We've no time for
your wishful thinking.
The information's true.
I simply know it.
Oh, you're an oracle now?
I told you to shut your trap
and to get some training
on a Knightmare, you dumbass!
[C.C.]
Dumbass? Oh really?
It's been ages since
anyone's dared to refer to me
in such a rude manner.
[TAMAKI] Like Zero's
mistress has any right
to get uppity with us!
[C.C.]
I said you were wrong.
You're a man who
only has vulgar ideas.
You've got a lot of nerve
talking to your
superior like that!
Look, this whole conversation's
gotten out of hand!
Okay, how about this?
We hang in a safe zone.
An ocean area just out
of detection range
where we wait until
the end of tomorrow.
How does that sound
for a time limit?
All right.
Well, I suppose
we have no choice.
[ALL chattering]
[C.C.]
For heaven's sake!
I was forced to talk
with that boring little man,
thanks to your silly prank.
You sent Kallen to the island?
You have very poor taste
for being such
an imperious observer.
[EUPHEMIA] What's wrong?
They're quite tasty!
[EUPHEMIA]
I'm sure you'll be able to make
your pitfall trap tomorrow.
[KALLEN] Oh...
I can't eat another bite!
Boy, am I stuffed!
So is this a glimpse
of what you're really like?
Yeah, ya wanna
make somethin' of it?
[SUZAKU] No, I think
it's charming to see you
so much livelier
than you are at school.
[gasps]
Hmph!
Kallen...
Leave the Black Knights.
It's not too late.
A captured terrorist never
winds up with a happy ending.
I thought you weren't so bad,
and then you showed
your true colors.
Well that won't work.
I happen to be the
captain of Zero's elite guard.
And in fact,
I fought you in my Knightmare.
Were you that red one?
[KALLEN]
Yeah.
And even if I lose
my life doing it,
I'll beat that
Knightmare of yours someday.
Using Zero's methods
offers no future.
And what about
your future, then?!
To just live the life of a
conqueror's subjugated lap dog?!
An honorary Britannian?!
Or to be the knight of
the third princess?! Ha!
The name of Genbu Kururugi,
the Last Samurai, weeps!
I am not you!
The world is wrong,
and I'm trying to change it!
If I don't--
If I don't, my brother's death
will have been for nothing.
That's my reason for fighting!
And I'll do whatever
it takes to win!
[SUZAKU]
Kallen, the truth is...
I killed my father.
[SUZAKU] My father
didn't commit suicide.
I took his life.
With this hand.
The stars haven't
changed, have they?
They were the same back then.
Long ago, we all used to gaze up
at the stars together.
Wouldn't it be wonderful if we
could live like that again?
I'd be so happy then.
Can't we go back to that?
Yes, you're right.
It would be so good to
just go back to how things were.
[SUZAKU] Zero is
a lot like my father.
He firmly believes
that the entire world
revolves around him.
That's why he's able to
justify spilling the blood
of so many people--
[KALLEN] That's why you accept
the way things are now?!
You call that peace?!
Some things are more important
than your life, you know!
It isn't that I
want you to give up.
I just want you
to ask yourself:
When you gain results
the wrong way,
what are you
left with in the end?
Only dark regret
and a deep emptiness
that have nowhere to go.
Then explain something.
What higher purpose did
the death of my brother serve?
Who gets to sit in judgment?
Who decides whether
it's right or wrong?
[LELOUCH] Euphy...
Even for me to survive...
[SUZAKU] Even struggling
with my shame...
I still search for a
reason to go on living.
I'm a disgrace.
[SCHNEIZEL] We couldn't find
major Kururugi washed ashore
on the other island.
So it's obvious
we should look here.
[BARTLEY] We'll send out a
search party in the morning.
Hm... And this must be
what you mentioned?
Yes.
We uncovered it when the
Shinjuku incident occurred.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Ahh...
Yes, I can see why this would
have attracted Clovis' interest.
Are you sure
you really saw a light?
[SUZAKU]
Yeah, I'm positive.
[LELOUCH]
It must be a search party.
Once we learn who it is,
we'll know how deal with them.
Deal with them?
[LLOYD]
A thought elevator, you say?
I'm afraid archeology
isn't my strong suit,
especially this
paranormal stuff!
[BARTLEY]
Why you...!
Show some respect!
[LLOYD] As I was saying,
this is way outside of my field.
I wish you could have
asked Cecile about this instead.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Please don't complain so much.
My father is infatuated
with this as well.
Isn't that right, Bartley?
[BARTLEY]
Yes.
We've found artifacts
similar to these
in a number of places
around the world.
Except for this one
that I discovered,
all the other sites are are
directly under imperial control.
This is mere
speculation on my part,
but I think the real reason
we're invading other countries
is to obtain these objects.
And so,
in order to analyze
this ancient occult data,
you're going to use
the Gawain's Druid System,
untuned prototype that it is?
[SCHNEIZEL]
That's why we called you in.
[LLOYD]
A-ha!
[LELOUCH] I think it
was right around here.
[EUPHEMIA] Lelouch,
if it is a search party,
then will our time
be over here?
Yes, it will.
[chuckles] I'm such
an undependable knight,
I couldn't even
capture you any food!
And besides,
that's a job reserved
for a real knight.
Your knight.
Suzaku Kururugi.
Mind if I ask you?
Why choose
an honorary Britannian?
Well, I...
[LELOUCH] What are those
two doing together?!
Suzaku!
P-Princess Euphemia?!
[ZERO]
Don't move!
This girl is my prisoner!
Zero!
[ZERO]
Just follow my cue.
I'll take back my
subordinate you have there!
We'll exchange prisoners!
Zero!
Once again, you--
[ZERO]
Keep back!
Ha! You find
my actions cowardly?
[ZERO chuckling]
[ZERO] Eliminate terrorists,
no matter what the sacrifice.
Do you intend
to follow this rule
and let your mistress die?
In spite of the fact
that your integrity
has already been broken?
[KALLEN yells]
Leave him alone!
Shut up, you royal puppet!
You're useless!
You can't think for yourself
or do anything on your own!
What?!
I'm not afraid of you,
and I don't care
what happens to me!
Suzaku, I command you to fight!
[ZERO]
Your Highness!
[SUZAKU]
With pleasure!
[ZERO]
You hardheaded fool!
[LLOYD]
Oh... not good.
[BARTLEY] Agh! My lord,
please save yourself!
Major Kururugi!
And is that...
...Zero?
Don't shoot, you fools!
Princess Euphemia's with them!
Capture them! Capture them!
[ZERO]
Tsk!
Look, Zero!
That's a Knightmare over there!
[ZERO]
Perfect!
We'll use that! Let's go!
Right!
[EUPHEMIA]
Suzaku!
[SOLDIERS grunting]
Suzaku, what is it,
what's wrong?
[ZERO]
This is good!
Not only unmanned,
but activated, too!
[SOLDIER] Form a wall in
front of Princess Euphemia!
Hurry!
[ZERO] What kind
of Knightmare is this?
[ZERO chuckles]
It's my lucky day!
[ZERO]
Schneizel!
So that's him? That's Zero?
[LLOYD]
Agh! The Gawain!
Stop that woman now!
Get that machine back!
We cannot allow it to
fall into Zero's hands!
[ZERO]
Schneizel!
Next time!
[COMM ALERT 1]
Alert 1! Alert 1!
Sutherlands are
blocking our exit!
[ZERO]
Hang on tight!
I'm going through them!
[KALLEN]
Huh?!
[ZERO]
Disappear.
[KALLEN yells]
[ZERO] Damn!
The weapons are incomplete!
Zero! Reinforcements!
Don't be worried yet.
Another system is operational!
We're flying?
This Knightmare can fly!
[laughing]
The Gawain!
Our beautiful prized Gawain!
Well, it was
only a test model.
Aside from that, I'm
thankful you're both all right.
Oh Schneizel, I missed you!
Dear Euphy,
I'm sorry it took us so long.
[EUPHEMIA]
No, it's all right!
[DEFENSE UNIT CAPT]
Your Highness,
shall we keep
to the schedule?
Oh. Right.
[EUPHEMIA]
Uh...
Major Suzaku Kururugi,
you're under
arrest for violation
of military regulations.
What's the meaning of this?!
Major Kururugi's my knight!
You can't do--
This is something
I can take care of later.
For now, let them be.
[EUPHEMIA]
Um, did something happen?
[ZERO]
I've contacted Ohgi!
We'll rendezvous
with them out at sea.
[KALLEN] Right!
And one other thing...
The Guren MK-II...?
It was recovered.
You may thank Asahina
and Chiba for that.
Yes, sir!
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku, forgive me.
I never intended to
use the power on you, but...
[ZERO]
Live!
[FAYER] Major Kururugi,
follow your orders!
[SUZAKU]
Shut up!
Who cares about them?!
I have to live!
[FAYER] I have no idea how you
got out of the Lancelot.
But you blew
a golden opportunity
to put an end to Zero in
order to save your own life,
according to this.
Are you going
to protest this evidence?
Was that... really me?
[FAYER] This is nothing less
than insubordination!
[CORNELIA]
Kururugi did that?
[STAFF B]
Yes. The details are unknown.
[CORNELIA]
Dammit.
And just when I thought we had
nailed the lid on Ishikawa.
[GUILFORD]
Your Highness!
[CORNELIA]
What now, Guilford?
The enemy has destroyed
the Great Kanmon Bridge
in Kyushu block!
What?!
[GUILFORD] They also
cut off vehicle access
at four other points,
and large numbers
of assault landing craft
are moving into the Genkai Sea!
[CORNELIA]
The Chinese Federation?!
But have they made
a declaration of war?
[GUILFORD]
No, Highness!
The craft are bearing
the flag of Japan!
[LELOUCH] What was Schneizel
doing on that island?
Was there something
hidden in that area?
And Euphy...
I think I can
trust you for now,
but I also need to consider what
happened with Kallen and Suzaku.
No!
First, we have
to deal with Kyushu!
That will determine our future.
The future of both the
Black Knights and myself!