[SUZAKU grunts]
[SUZAKU gasps]
You woke up too soon.
Uh-- Huh?
C.C.!
[ANYA]
What exactly are you doing here?
Somehow, I get the feeling that
you didn't come
to help out Charles.
[SUZAKU]
Anya... What are you...?
Well, at the moment,
I'm the mother of
Lelouch and Nunnally.
I am Marianne.
[gasps]
[OHGI]
Yeah.
I'm about to apprise Lady Kaguya
and General Commander
Xing-ke of the situation.
I don't know if they're
going to understand or not.
But clearly, there's
one thing to do.
Yeah, I know.
Which is--we gotta make
sure that Zero is dead.
[KALLEN]
I need to find out for sure.
From Lelouch.
Otherwise... I'll never...
I'll never be able to move on.
So...
...since we have
plenty of time now...
Will you answer me?
Who was it that
killed my mother?
And what's your excuse
for not protecting her?
[EMPEROR]
How ironic.
Here you are, seeking the truth.
You, who made it this far
only by your deception
and your lies.
[LELOUCH]
That's true.
I've lied every step of the way.
And not just about
my name and past.
I've hidden my
true intentions, too.
But that's pragmatism, isn't it?
People need to play
along with each other.
We melt into a place.
If we didn't, then
nations and people...
...these things called
"communities" wouldn't exist.
Everyone uses lies.
On family. On friends.
In society.
And everyone wears
a different face.
But... is that a sin?
What is one's true face?
Even you wear a mask--
That of an emperor.
None of us can make a move now
without our respective personas.
[EMPEROR]
You're wrong.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
When we realize that lies
have no meaning in the
endlessness of eternity,
those personas will vanish.
When we understand each other,
conflict will disappear.
That all sounds
like metaphysical
nonsense to me.
[EMPEROR]
It will soon be reality.
[LELOUCH grunts]
[EMPEROR] You see, this is
my Ragnarock Connection.
Soon, these masks
known as deceit
will be discarded by the world,
revealing the truth.
[SUZAKU]
Cs' world?
[C.C.]
In current terminology,
it's the collective unconscious.
A collective of peoples'
minds with memories.
The sea of transmigration.
The great consciousness.
Some refer to it as "God."
Was that what I saw
when we met at Narita?
[C.C.] There, it was mixed with
your personal consciousness.
I'm merely guessing, as I don't
know what it was you saw.
[SUZAKU]
How irresponsible.
Do you like having others
peep into your mind?
It's people.
They're masks are the
collective unconsciousness.
Windows that open into
their minds and memories.
And the minds of people are--
[ANYA]
Oh, forget it.
It's too messed up for me to do.
C.C., could you please?
[C.C.]
Do you really plan to go in?
Yes, of course!
Charles has been waiting
for us, after all.
This would have been so easy
if you'd only
given him your Code.
Oh... I'll go first, all right?
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
What are you doing?!
You know, Suzaku--
You and I--we're very similar.
Similar?
In the way that
we both wish to die
and yet are unable to.
[BISMARCK]
Hm? Prince Schneizel...
...and the Black Knights?!
[KALLEN]
Stay alive, Lelouch!
I've got an question that
I still want to ask you!
Wha--?! It can't be!
[MARIANNE]
My, Lelouch! How you've grown!
M-Mother?!
[EMPEROR]
Marianne, I see you've come.
Is this an illusion?!
You'd do this?!
[MARIANNE]
No.
It really is me, Lelouch.
However, I can only take
on my original appearance
while I'm present
within this system.
It really is...?
[EMPEROR]
Lelouch, I will now answer
your previous question.
[LELOUCH]
Tch!
[EMPEROR] Half a century ago,
my elder brother and I
existed in a hell on Earth.
Our family was just rivals
competing for the throne.
Assassinations occurred
with regularity.
Daily betrayals spawned by lies.
Killing each other off.
My own mother fell victim to it.
My brother and I were sickened
and angered by the world.
We therefore both swore an oath.
To create a world without lies.
[MARIANNE] Both C.C. and I
agreed to this as well.
V.V., however...
[MARIANNE]
What did you call me for today?
I've cleared everyone
out of here.
I even had Cornelia withdraw.
[V.V.]
Sorry to do this.
Especially without
Charles around.
[MARIANNE] Is this about
the sword of Akasha?
[V.V.] Hm? Oh, no. This is
only about Charles.
Ever since he met you,
Charles has been
acting like a different man.
It seems to me that you
and he have come to enjoy
learning more about one another.
You realize that,
if this continues,
the contract we made
will never be fulfilled.
I'll be left alone.
[MARIANNE]
Hm?
From the beginning of time,
it's always been the woman
who's lead the man astray.
[gasps]
[GUARD 1]
Lady Marianne.
[MARIANNE]
I told you to stay out of here!
[gasps]
[GUARDS groaning]
The job is done.
Right. Begin the cover-up.
Maybe we can make Nunnally
out to be the witness.
It's imperative that
this looks like
it was the work of terrorists.
[MARIANNE]
Anya Alstreim...
The young girl who had arrived
a week earlier to be
schooled in etiquette.
[MARIANNE]
My Geass power was to cross over
into another person's mind.
[MARIANNE] The power that had
been dormant for so long,
activated for the first
time as I was dying.
I hid inside Anya to save myself
from being killed by V.V.
And then, I realized.
Realized that when my
consciousness surfaced,
I could communicate
mind-to-mind with C.C...
When she discovered the truth,
C.C. left the
directorship to V.V.,
and then disappeared.
[EMPEROR] I spoke with my
brother about it, however...
I heard. What a tragedy.
I shall miss Marianne.
[growls]
[EMPEROR]
My brother lied to me!
After we had sworn
to create a world
without deceit!
Agh! How dare you!
Don't try to pass off blame
for everything on the dead!
Nunnally and I!
You sent us to
Japan as hostages!
[EMPEROR]
It was necessary!
Necessary for what?!
What kind of parent does that?!
If you have someone
you don't want to lose,
you should keep
them at a distance.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[PRODUCER]
Milly!
Uh, when the sun rises,
I wanna get a shot
with ground zero
in the background.
[MILLY]
Okay, gotcha.
[A.D.] Sorry about this.
Relief will be here from Niigata
and Nagoya by afternoon,
so hang tight.
[MILLY]
I'm okay.
[gasps]
[BISMARCK] Right now, we're
suppressing the rebel forces
with the aid of
the Black Knights.
However...
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hm? Is there something else?
[BISMARCK]
Prince Schneizel...
Just how much do you know?
[SCHNEIZEL] How frightening!
What are you referring to?
[C.C.]
I used Lelouch.
I was fully aware of the
truth the entire time.
In order to bring
about my own death,
I had to make his
survival a priority.
[SUZAKU]
Any regrets?
[C.C.]
Not really.
My sensibilities
are quite different
as an immortal witch.
I abandoned my
humanity long ago.
[SUZAKU]
We aren't all alike, you know.
[C.C.]
Huh?
C.C., I want you to send
me to the other world.
Regardless that you
may think I'm foolish,
I can't wait here
and do nothing!
[EMPEROR]
That's right.
I sent both you and
your sister to Japan
to escape my brother's sight.
That's also why I had Marianne's
body secretly taken away.
[MARIANNE]
As long as my body still exists,
there's the possibility that
I'll be able to return to it.
[EMPEROR] Anya and Nunnally
became witnesses.
Therefore, it was necessary
to rewrite their memories
in order to protect everything.
Nunnally?!
You mean her blindness isn't
psychosomatic after all, but--!
Even though she
was a false witness,
there remained a very real
danger she would be killed.
[EMPEROR]
To ensure Nunnally's safety,
proof was needed that would
lead far away from the truth.
[MARIANNE]
The original plan called
for only one immortal Code.
However, for research
to progress,
we had to have
an additional Code.
In other words, without C.C.,
we didn't have a 100% guarantee
that it would succeed.
[EMPEROR] When Marianne was
unable to persuade C.C.
to help us, we were
left with no choice.
We were forced to
use you, Lelouch.
[LELOUCH] Then... What was
the point of me doing this?
These tragedies will
no longer be necessary
once the Ragnarock
Connection is established.
Masks will vanish.
Then everyone can be exactly
who they're supposed to be.
[LELOUCH]
I see...
All the battle and
bloodshed between
Britannia and the Black Knights
was done just
to lure out C.C...
Well then, it seems that from
the very beginning,
I was merely a nuisance.
Just a ruckus in the world.
[laughs]
And, what do you two
think of all this?
Did you already know that
I was going to
come here, Lelouch?
[LELOUCH] And that you
regained your memories, too.
It was necessary for
this plan, wasn't it?
[EMPEROR]
Precisely.
Therefore, I cannot
see any sense
in your coming here
as well, Kururugi.
[SUZAKU]
I'm sure you can't.
I heard you were
already immortal.
That's why there's something
I want to know for certain.
Why did you make this
thing? For what reason?
Why?
Because it's what Nunnally
and Euphy both desired.
They wanted a gentle world.
Now I see. It's obvious.
The time is here.
C.C., since we
are all assembled,
the plan can commence now.
I will grant your wish after
everything has been completed.
[voices wailing]
[demonic roaring]
[rumbling]
What the--?
Where am I?
All over the world?
[KANON]
Yes.
Bismarck?
It must be His Majesty's
plan coming to fruition.
If His Majesty succeeds
in carrying out his vision,
then whatever is
left of the world
will be yours to govern,
per his royal decree.
Although...
The sense of politics
will have changed greatly.
Behold! It's begun!
The Sword of Akasha
is slaying God!
Now... Once our marks
of Geass become one,
the old world will cease and
the new world will spring forth!
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch.
What was your
motivation for wanting
to control the world?
Don't waste my time, Suzaku.
You know it was Nunnally.
Or are you just using
her as your excuse?
[LELOUCH chuckles]
Yes, you're right.
I am.
I have fought to protect
everything I thought
I wanted to protect.
[SUZAKU] If you're going
to achieve that end,
you need to take action.
[LELOUCH]
Yes.
The means to that end requires
me to reject something.
[SUZAKU]
Which is...?
[LELOUCH]
That... I...
[EMPEROR]
Hm?
[LELOUCH]
I reject you!
And I reject everything
you believe!
Why do people lie?
It isn't only because they
struggle against each other.
It's also because there's
something that they're seeking!
[C.C.]
Ah...
You now want a world
without change. How stagnant!
You could hardly call it life!
The same as a world of memories!
Just a world that's
closed and completed!
That's a place I
wouldn't wanna live in!
But, Lelouch...
Are you saying you're
rejecting me, as well?
That depends.
Is your desire the same
as His Majesty's, Mother?
[MARIANNE] It will be so good
to rejoin all the people
from whom we've been separated.
You can be reunited with
those who have died.
Even Euphemia.
[SUZAKU grunts]
As I expected.
You both believe
that this new world
you envision will
be best for all.
But forcing your good
intentions on others
is no different
from an evil act!
In time, the people
will come to accept it.
[LELOUCH]
That time will never come!
Only one thing is
undeniably certain.
I understand now that what
you did to Nunnally and me
may have been done out of
good intentions. But...
The hard fact remains
that you abandoned us
in a foreign land!
But we did that to protect you!
[LELOUCH]
Then why didn't you stop the war
between Japan and Britannia?!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] The plan was such
a priority for you both,
that it didn't matter to either
of you if Nunnally and I
were alive or dead.
That's why you abandoned us!
All you have left are
self-serving excuses!
[MARIANNE]
Lelouch, you're wrong!
You just told me!
You said that the dead
will rejoin the living!
You don't give a damn
about the future!
[EMPEROR] The future is
the Ragnarok Connection!
Once it's finally done,
the gentler existence
that Nunnally spoke of will--!
Stop it!
The world you're speaking of
will be kinder and gentler
only for you!
The world that
my sister wished for
is one in which kindness
is extended to everyone,
even strangers.
[SUZAKU]
He may be right.
At the very least, Euphy never
said that Lelouch was Zero,
even to the very end. Shirley
didn't either! That's why I...!
Let's say it was
true. What of it?
There's nothing to
be done about it.
The Ragnarok Connection
has begun!
You think so?
I am Zero!
The man who works miracles!
our Geass power will
have no effect on me!
Nor will it on anyone else here!
[LELOUCH]
No.
There's someone else
here, isn't there?
Huh?
That's right!
Cs' World is the will
of mankind itself!
And all men are not equal!
Remember those words?
They're your own!
And because of that,
I'm sure you realize
that my power will work!
[EMPEROR]
You're a fool, Lelouch!
God cannot be defeated by
the power of the king!
[LELOUCH]
I don't intend to defeat God!
This is a request! Yes!
Now I know who I really am!
God!
Collective unconscious!
[gasps]
[moaning]
Please, don't stop
the march of time!
Lelouch, you
ungrateful child--Agh!
Nobody would have wanted this!
No one! And
especially not Euphy!
And I saved you
so that you could
talk to Euphy again!
Meaning you were going
to force me to, right?!
You can't do this, boy!
Not against God, nor all
of humanity itself!
[LELOUCH]
Regardless, what I want...
...is tomorrow!
[gasps]
It can't be!
The Thought Elevator is falling!
The dream that I...
and Marianne...
...and my brother all shared...
[C.C.]
Charles, just stop already.
It was presumptuous of us
to even attempt this.
[EMPEROR] C.C.! We still
bear the marks of Geass!
No matter what occurs, we--
This isn't a falsehood, Father.
It's reality's response.
[MARIANNE]
Darling?! You--!
[EMPEROR]
No! It's not possible!
I'm supposed to be immortal!
We're being absorbed?
Consumed by Cs' World?!
But what about C.C.?!
Why isn't she
disappearing, as well?!
You supported this plan
as much as we did!
[C.C.]
Sorry. But I finally realized.
The love you have
is only for yourselves.
No, that's not true at all!
We love our children very much!
You have any idea
what the meaning is
behind Nunnally's
beautiful smile?
Ah-- The meaning?
Why don't you understand?!
Nunnally was blinded!
My own sister was crippled!
She knew!
She knew that there
were things in this world
that she would never be
able to do by herself!
So her smile--
Nunnally's smile...
...was her way of
expressing gratitude!
[EMPEROR] You're laboring
under a delusion!
I will not let you
call that a lie!
Over my dead body!
Your refusal to face reality!
Content to watch us from afar!
Don't make me laugh!
There's only one truth here!
You, my own parents...
You abandoned us!
--[MARIANNE gasps]
--[EMPEROR growls]
You clever little fool...!
Suzaku!
Stay out of this!
[EMPEROR] Can't you understand
that If you refuse me
and what I offer, you
will inherit his world!
Schneizel's world!
Do not judge me!
Good and evil intentions are
on each side of the same card!
Even then, you still have--
No matter what,
I'll always reject
the world you envision.
Be gone now!
[screams]
[MARIANNE, EMPEROR screaming]
[BISMARCK gasps]
It can't be!
Can I assume that...?
Yes. His Majesty has now been--!
[LELOUCH]
C.C... are you going, as well?
[C.C.] When death comes,
you want to at least
be smiling, right?
And, you two?
What are you planning to do now?
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[C.C.]
You rejected Charles' plan.
Instead, you chose reality
and the forward march of time.
However...
I know.
Lelouch is the person
who murdered Euphy.
What of it?
[MILLY] It has been one month
since the destruction
caused by the
F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
Today, His Majesty
Emperor Charles
will make an
important announcement
to the entire nation.
We will be bringing you
live international coverage
of this from Pendragon
imperial palace.
Even though His
Majesty has not made
any public appearances
in the past month--
[CAROLINE]
Didn't somebody say
that the emperor was missing?
[GUINEVERE] Bismarck was
the one who reported that,
and now he's gone.
As for Schneizel and the
others, where are they?
Don't know.
There's been no word
from Cambodia yet.
Presenting his Imperial Majesty!
[PALACE GUESTS murmuring]
[ODYSSEUS]
Hm?!
But that's not...
Where's His Majesty?
What the hell?!
Wha...?! It can't be!
But how?
There's no way!
[PALACE GUESTS murmuring]
[LELOUCH]
Greetings.
I am Lelouch vi Britannia
of the royal family.
99TH emperor of the realm.
Good lord.
How can this be?!
I-It's really you?!
You're alive?
Yes, sister, I am.
I've returned from the
depths of hell intact.
[ODYSSEUS]
Lelouch, how good to see you!
When Nunnally was located,
I figured that you would
be found alive, too.
But now, aren't you
carrying this joke
a bit too far?
That's the throne
of our father--
Charles zi Britannia,
the 98th emperor,
no longer lives. And I'm
the one who took his life.
--Huh?!
--[PALACE GUESTS gasp]
[LELOUCH] Therefore... that
makes me the next emperor!
[CAROLINE] What are you
saying?! Are you nuts?!
Guards, take that fool
and execute him!
He's guilty of
murdering our emperor!
[PALACE GUARDS groan]
Suzaku! But why?!
[LELOUCH] May I introduce...
Suzaku Kururugi.
My knight.
A Knight of the Round
above all others.
I grant him the title
"Knight of Zero."
Suzaku?! They're
working together?!
[ODYSSEUS] Lelouch, Sir
Kururugi, this just won't do.
Pulling a bad stunt like this
on an international broadcast!
Do you think so?
Let me make this easy
for you all to understand.
Acknowledge me as emperor!
Lelouch, I insist that you
stop joking around like--
We hear and obey, Your Majesty!
[CAROLINE, GUINEVERE]
All hail Emperor Lelouch!
[PALACE GUESTS chanting] All
hail Lelouch! All hail Lelouch!
I need to thank you, Lelouch.
Now that you've
reappeared on the scene,
we no longer have a
problem to contend with.
But why is Kururugi helping
him? What's his reason?
He succeeds in
furthering himself
by continually betraying others.
Don't be concerned.
Let Lelouch have all of it,
because it doesn't matter.
He can have Britannia,
the whole nation.
The question is,
what comes next?
Which will control the world?
Will it be Lelouch's Geass
power? Or will it be...?
[LELOUCH] There is nothing
that is unforgivable.
It's only the willingness
not to forgive.
That was something
Shirley once told Suzaku.
And that was the starting
point in the conversation
I had with him.
The starting point
to face reality.
There is nothing
that Suzaku and I
can't accomplish together.
[LELOUCH chuckles]
How ironic.
I, the one who has
perpetually rejected
and denounced Britannia...