[LELOUCH]
The world continues moving on,
thanks to miracles
which Zero has performed.
The world is being reborn,
thanks to actions
which Zero has taken.
Yes. The world is moving to
the next stage, as it should.
Against conflicting emotions,
Zero must carry on.
For the hands which mark time
cannot be stopped.
The Emperor's gone?
He's disappeared?
He has.
I've just received word
from Prime Minister Schneizel
about it.
It's important that we
restrict this information
to only those present here.
He also said that
this situation is only known
to a handful of people
in the homeland.
[GUILFORD]
What on earth happened to him?
[NUNNALLY] There is no news
on the investigation.
Hold on a minute.
Won't this affect our plans to
attack the Chinese Federation?
If His Majesty isn't present
to issue a
declaration of war,
then we can't do anything!
And there's domestic security.
If the Numbers were
to learn of this situation,
you had better have
new policies in place.
Well I'd...
[LOHMEYER] People expect
action from authority figures!
Uh, Miss Lohmeyer?
Do you think you'd like
to handle it alone?
[LOHMEYER]
Sorry. I meant no disrespect.
[SUZAKU]
Is this for the best?
With the Emperor gone,
Nunnally should
be safe for now, but...
[LELOUCH]
I've done it!
The actions which
Britannia has taken
prove the Emperor is absent.
It's seems he is truly
trapped in the other realm.
Though I am concerned
about what he said before,
I am content simply knowing
that Nunnally is safe.
[C.C.]
Um, what should I be doing now?
Let's see now...
Sing me a song
while hopping on one foot
and wearing your
clothes inside out.
[C.C.]
Yes. Right away, master.
Wha--?
No, wait! I was kidding!
[C.C. gasps]
I'm sorry!
Please don't beat me hard again!
[LELOUCH] Her mind has
completely reverted.
She's now only the slave girl
before the power of Geass came.
Don't you worry.
I would never do anything
to harm you at all.
It's the truth.
I promise you.
--[beeping noise]
--[JEREMIAH] Master Lelouch.
[LELOUCH]
Yes, Jeremiah. What is it?
I see. You got her out of there,
inside of the
Sutherland's cockpit.
[JEREMIAH]
Please forgive me.
You ordered me
to destroy them all,
but killing a member of
the Britannian royal family
was just...
[LELOUCH]
Forget it.
Or rather,
I should say, well done.
Tell me, Lelouch,
what is it you are seeking
within that accursed power?
[LELOUCH]
What am I seeking?
I'm seeking to save
a sister that I adore.
[CORNELIA]
How dare you!
[ASAHINA]
Kinoshita.
[KINOSHITA]
Captain Asahina!
[ASAHINA]
I see. Bloodstains.
I'd sure like to know...
What was Zero doing?
Well I...
[ROLO]
...won't say a thing.
Those are Zero's orders.
The details are top secret.
Even General Tohdoh
isn't allowed to know.
[ASAHINA] You toss real
confident weight around
for a newbie.
Value in this team
is gained by confidence.
And confidence is earned by a
Black Knight from Zero himself.
That's some
trusting value system.
[SUZAKU]
I'm so sorry!
What the hell's that mean?!
There's no need to apologize!
It's either right or wrong!
You think you can flip
on the good guy routine
whenever you like?!
Not when I'm this pissed off!
Kallen Kouzuki's a soldier,
not a sideshow!
[KALLEN]
Hmph!
I'm mostly pissed off
because you're not resisting.
[SUZAKU groans]
[KALLEN]
There. Put me to death.
An inmate assaulting
a Knight of the Round
should be a good reason
enough for anyone.
[SUZAKU]
No, I won't.
Because I'm the one
who did wrong.
"No, I won't."
I hate you!
[ZERO]
And so,
by ratifying this charter, it
will give birth to an alliance
that will rival the
Holy Britannian Empire.
And its name shall be...
...The United
Federation Of Nations!
[ALL gasp]
It's wonderful, Master Zero!
There are exiled regimes
throughout the
Britannian colonies.
Some have agreed to participate.
With this move,
we've finally earned
a just cause to launch
a war of liberation!
A just cause
to launch war...
If the forthcoming
operation to recapture Japan
is indeed successful,
then other undecided nations
will join us
in a chain reaction.
[EMPRESS]
Mm-hmm.
[ZERO]
And it will succeed,
but we must form the U.F.N.
before Britannia can act!
Time decides our
victory or defeat.
I ask only that you cooperate
on the focus of our plan.
I know representatives
here must discuss the needs
of their individual countries.
But remember...
What you decide will change
the course of world history!
[ALL cheering]
[C.C. gasps]
Hi, everyone! How are you?
I'm so sorry!
[MILLY] It's an up-and-coming
one-woman festival
with Milly Ashford here!
[ANCHOR] Well you're
not exactly alone, you know.
[MILLY]
Guess what, audience?
We're going to the jungle,
right here in the city!
[ANCHOR]
We are?
[MILLY]
Animal time!
And that means hot topics
with Trend Watch!
[LELOUCH]
I brought you some food to eat.
[TV continues in background]
[LELOUCH]
It's only me.
[C.C.]
Huh?
[LELOUCH]
It's called pizza.
I'd think you be hungry by now.
I really wanted
you to have some,
so I asked Sugiyama
to help me out.
You don't remember, do you?
Go ahead. Try it.
[LELOUCH]
It's all right. You can eat.
[C.C.]
Okay!
It's good, isn't it?
[C.C.] Oh, yes,
yes! It's really, really good!
Thought so.
I'm glad you like it.
[LELOUCH] Prez,
I'm not sure that's the way
to start out a new career.
[C.C. gasps]
I see. That's right.
You don't even know
what this is, do you?
[ANYA]
Troubled mind?
Nothing but trouble.
Even though I chose it myself.
Decisions I made
eight years back.
[ANYA] Do you still
place trust in him?
The you from eight years ago?
[SUZAKU] Are you asking if
the choices I made were foolish?
Memories that people
have are always vague.
No point in believing in them.
I'd have to disagree with that.
[ANYA]
But I know it.
In my case...
I kept a diary
from nine years ago.
I don't remember
anything from it at all.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[ANYA]
And there's more I don't trust.
The data I stored doesn't
match any memories I have.
[SUZAKU]
Could that be it?
The Emperor's Geass?
But why use it on Anya?
Even recent things.
My memories don't match
the recordings at all.
Like when fighting with
the Chinese Federation,
they don't...
[hisses]
[LUCIANO] What do people value
most, Sir Kururugi the traitor?
Their own life, of course.
So I see that
you've returned
from the Belarusian Front,
Sir Bradley.
[hisses]
It's the Knight of Ten.
[LUCIANO] I see your skill
at courting with the new ladies
is still intact.
Princess Massacre
wasn't enough for you?
Speak another
untrue word of her name
and you will have to
face me in a duel, sir.
[LUCIANO] Oh.
It's seems you've forgotten.
I'm very well known as
the "Genius of Homicide."
Perhaps being only a Number
without any true bloodline
has dulled your...
They sent the Galahad?!
[BISMARCK] Both of you!
Cease your squabbling!
The Knight of One.
But why would they send
Bismarck Waldstein here?
Anya, a foolish question.
Obviously The Black Knights
will invade Area 11 first.
Luciano.
I've brought the Valkyrie
Squadron for that here as well.
I have also readied
Gareths for this event.
Now is the time for us
to join our forces
under the command
of Prince Schneizel.
So save your solo flaunting
for the battlefield!
Hah! I understand it well.
Whatever you say, my lord.
[NUNNALLY, KALLEN laughing]
[KALLEN] So Lelouch
always acted like that, huh?
[NUNNALLY] My big brother
can be so stubborn at times,
but actually,
he's really very kind.
My brother Naoto
was like that as well.
[LUCIANO] Oh! I'd heard we had
captured the Black Knight Ace,
but I didn't expect to
find such a lovely young girl.
[NUNNALLY] I don't believe
I gave you permission
to enter this area,
Sir Bradley.
[KALLEN gasps]
[LUCIANO]
My apologies, Your Highness.
[KALLEN]
Well...
So you're the
Vampire of Britannia?
[LUCIANO]
Yes.
It's a shame we're
not on a battlefield
or I could savor
your blood as well.
Pity.
So, are you here to
finish off the hostage?
Not so.
Hostages have only
one value I care for.
It seems to
hold dear its own life.
And while alive,
one can do anything he
has a whim for to its body.
Have you no sense
of pride, Dear Sir Bradley?
Threatening an unarmed,
imprisoned woman.
[LUCIANO]
The naïve child.
Still getting by
on family laurels?
[GINO]
Hmm...
Tell me.
Are you implying
that it's easy to become
a Knight Of The Round
on family recognition alone?
[CECILE]
Huh?!
Mount the F.L.E.I.J.A
onto the Lancelot?
[LLOYD] Well the intention
was for Suzaku
to pilot the Guren, but...
The Guren?
Sorry, he's right.
I got so carried away I forgot.
It's just Lloyd and I
got so wrapped up
in our little hobby, we...
[SUZAKU]
Hobby?
[LLOYD] Rakshata's mechanisms
are quite easy to tinker with.
Now it's so souped-up
it can't be flown!
End result, you're our
little devicer again!
[NINA]
Excuse me, Professor Lloyd,
now that you mention
the Lancelot...
[LLOYD] You wouldn't
mix up a strategic weapon
with a tactical one, would you?
[NINA]
I have thought it through.
Any matter caught within
the primary area of effect field
will be annihilated
by the F.L.E.I.J.A.'s
rapid sphere collapse.
Hold on!
You want Suzaku to
fire a weapon like that?!
He'd kill his own people.
A massacre.
Suzaku, you don't
consider yourself an Eleven
anymore, right?
That's why I want to entrust
the F.L.E.I.J.A. to you.
You'd give me that burden?
[NINA] You were
Princess Euphemia's knight,
so naturally...
[LLOYD]
Mm-mmm, Nina, darling.
A fine quandary
might just kill Suzaku,
and take you along as well!
[DIETHARD] Yes.
We've finished preparations
for our worldwide broadcast.
Lin Xing-ke and General Tohdoh
are in the waiting area.
Right.
Very good.
After I meet with the Indian
and Guinean members,
expect me at the assembly.
[LELOUCH]
Do not leave this room.
[C.C.]
Uh, okay.
And so, later...
[LELOUCH]
Later?
I mean, see you later.
Huh?
[laughs]
[LELOUCH]
I'll be off, then.
[EMPRESS] R-Regarding the union
of the nations charter,
I will leave
explanation of it
to Representative of the Supreme
Council, Kaguya Sumeragi.
[EMPRESS sighs]
Are you all right?
We could always--
No! I already got the--
You're the Empress.
We know you can.
[TAMAKI laughs]
Good thing we followed
old Zero, isn't it, buddy?!
Sure is.
[MINAMI]
By the way, where's C.C.?
[SUGIYAMA] I heard that
she was still feeling ill.
[TAMAKI]
Morning sickness, huh?
Congrats to Papa Zero!
[MINASE] Tamaki-san, maybe
you've had a little too much.
[TAMAKI]
Bring on the good stuff!
A soldier wearing
makeup is disgraceful.
I have to make you look good.
Um, sir...
After this current
situation is over...
I'd like to propose a request
to Kyoshiro Tohdoh that...
[MINAMI]
Great! You're finally here!
[SUGIYAMA] Is this any time
to be running late again?
[OHGI]
I know. Sorry, guys.
[TOHDOH]
Ohgi. Did you oversleep again?
Too slow.
Sorry I'm late,
but the truth is, uh...
[DIETHARD]
We're all here, let's go.
It's our day to change all
of the history books, right?
[REPORTER]
We are coming live to you
right over Horai Island.
Where the ratification ceremony
for the United States Charter
is about to begin!
[MILLY] To help viewers
understand this development,
the ceremony and ratification
of this new charter
will create a
federation of nations
that will rival our own empire.
As parts of the
now dissipating E.U.
are joining as well, it will
have a great unified power.
Included from the E.U.are:
Poland, Italy...
Can't reach
soldiers like Suzaku...
No brainer, but why can't
I contact Rolo or Lelouch?
The Black Knights have convinced
all of these these
representative nations
to participate.
Therefore the leader
behind this must be Zero.
In short, the U.F.N. will most
likely be an enemy to Britannia.
Military forces are deployed in
Kyushu, Chugoku, and Hokuriku.
[CROWD applauds]
[REPORTER] As everyone watching
this broadcast has witnessed,
all 47 nations
have just ratified
the United States Charter.
Please stay tuned...
[EDGAR] Lord Guilford,
we've finished preparations
for your troops review.
[GUILFORD]
Very good. On my way.
[phone rings]
[GUILFORD]
Yes?
Don't worry, if it's
about the troop review I...
[JEREMIAH]
Lord Guilford.
Orange boy?
[KANNON] They're forming a union
of nations, just as you said.
[BISMARCK] But the
militaries of each country
will never be able
to work together.
[LOHMEYER]
They'll just be an unruly mob.
No. There is an option.
[REPORTER] ...and those of
international accords,
this article takes precedence.
[KAGUYA] Finally, article 17
of the United States Charter.
All ratifying
nations do now declare
to abandon native
military power forever.
[NUNNALLY gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Abandon military power?
[LOHMEYER]
Are they mad?
To guarantee security,
member nations have agreed
to employ a fighting force
not affiliated
with any one country.
They have contracted
The Black Knights.
[ZERO]
We hereby accept.
Our acceptance also allows for
U.F.N. funding and
personnel involvement.
In return,
we will become the shield
to defend every member nation,
and its sword to oppose
any external foe!
The option, right?
[EMPRESS]
Disturbances in this world
are caused by military powers
of disparate nations.
The U.F.N. shall
only use military force
in accordance
with a full resolution
by the supreme council.
And with that,
I shall put forth
the first motion.
[KAGUYA] Japan is being held
by an unjust foreign power,
and the U.S.J.
have asked for our help
to free them
from this occupation.
I request that the Black Knights
be dispatched at once.
All those in favor
please stand up.
[KAGUYA] And so with
overwhelming majority,
under U.F.N.
resolution number 1,
the Black Knights shall now
go forth to liberate Japan.
[ZERO]
So be it!
Under U.F.N.
resolution number 1,
our first operational
objective shall be...
...Japan!
[CROWD cheers]
Our Japan.
And now we shall take it back!
Might rescue Kallen, also.
Huh? Yeah, we'll do that.
Hear me, Zero!
[ZERO]
What?!
[KNIGHT 1]
The system's hacked?!
[KNIGHT 2] It's coming in
from 14 external paths!
[SUZAKU]
The emperor!
[LUCIANO]
Well. Look who's back.
Was this fake disappearance
your doing, father? A charade?
Switch to the auxiliary lines!
Cut the link, dammit!
[KNIGHT 3]
We can't!
They've got those as well!
[EMPEROR] Zero. You thought this
foolishness would surprise me?
[LELOUCH]
Impossible! He's still alive?!
[EMPEROR]
However, it matters not.
This charter you've made
is a child's note.
The E.U., once a third
of the world, is now dead.
You've only helped
distinguish Britannia on a map
from the rest
of the pitiful dirt.
The situation is
very simple and clear.
For in the end whoever
succeeds in this battle
shall gain control
of the entire world.
Very well. Have at me, Zero.
I'm ready.
So will you win
it all now, Zero,
or will you lose everything?
Time to learn
the gambles of war.
All hail Britannia!
[CROWD] All hail Britannia!
[chanting continues]
[TOHDOH]
Long live Japan!
[CROWD]
All hail Britannia!
[chanting continues]
[CROWD]
Long live Japan!
[chanting continues]
[LELOUCH]
The emperor is still alive?
[C.C.]
Um, excuse me.
Welcome back.
[LELOUCH]
This isn't good.
Not good at all.
I have to rescue
Nunnally at once!
[LELOUCH] Maybe I could
use Cornelia some way.
No! The hostage ploy
would have no effect on him.
Perhaps use Jeremiah or Rolo?
No, I can't!
And Geass won't work on him!
Should I reveal to the world
that Zero's Lelouch?
No!
If the Black Knights
found out their leader
were an enemy prince,
I'd lose that too!
And rescuing Nunnally is useless
if there's no country
that will accept us!
Dammit! What should I do?!
Um, master, I kept this
last piece so you could have it.
You left without having
breakfast and must be hungry.
So please, if you--
[LELOUCH]
Be quiet!
[C.C. yelps]
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Hey...
Forgive me, master,
I'll clean it up at once!
[LELOUCH]
No. Leave it there!
Careful now, you're bleeding.
Uh... No. It's fine.
I'm okay.
I get cut up all the time.
[LELOUCH]
All the time?
Bleeding feels
even better when it's cold.
It feels warm on your outside.
It stings a bit,
but only on the outside,
and that's always better
than hurt on your inside.
It's just...
Any kind of warmth helps
make you try to keep going.
Oh, lookit, master,
you're shaking.
Are you cold now?
[LELOUCH]
Yeah, maybe. Maybe I am.
And the hurt on the inside...
How's it healed?
You just think of...
...some friends.
[C.C.]
I've never actually had one.
Not like families,
that always comes and goes.
I mean someone special
who stands beside you.
At least I guess that's what
I've heard that friends do...
Yes, they do.
[C.C.]
I'm right?
A friend will
stand by your side?
[LELOUCH]
Exactly right.
A friend is always there.
[phone ringing]
[SUZAKU]
I'm here.
It's Lelouch.
[SUZAKU]
I know.
[LELOUCH] Um, so...
Have you seen the news?
[SUZAKU] About Area 11
becoming a battlefield again?
Yes.
[LELOUCH]
The Tokyo Settlement.
It'll be in danger?
[SUZAKU]
Depends... on your decisions.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch. Are you Zero?
[LELOUCH gasps]
Yes, I am.
I am Zero.
[SUZAKU gasps]
Now tell me why an enemy
of Britannia is calling.
[LELOUCH]
Help me. Please save Nunnally.
The emperor has
been using her as hostage
to try and lure me
into his trap!
Don't you see?
That's why I've had
to operate in secret!
[LELOUCH]
Please, Suzaku!
You're the only person
I can turn to now!
[SUZAKU]
How dare you!
You think that request
means anything to me?!
[LELOUCH]
No, I don't.
But I need your help.
I need it now!
Always so selfish.
[LELOUCH]
Yes! You're all I have.
The only friend I can turn to!
Suzaku!
Protect her. It's Nunnally.
My heart's begging!
[SUZAKU]
Very well, then.
However... One condition.
I will protect Nunnally.
But you must come
to Area 11 by yourself,
where she is.
The place will be
the Kururugi shrine.
The two of us meet there.
Alone.
[LELOUCH]
With things as there are,
should I have forced
my way through
to save Nunnally much earlier?
But if I had,
I'd be forced to treat her
as an enemy hostage.
And she will never come
to me of her own free will.
With all this hatred
united against Britannia,
I can't stop the
malice that will now
be directed at Nunnally.
It's all too dangerous.
Right. Only one chance left.
All I have left is trust.
I need to trust Suzaku!