[EUPHEMIA] I, Euphemia li
Britannia, bid all of you
within the sound of my voice
to heed the following command!
Seek out any Japanese
you can find...
And please kill them!
Leave not a single
one of them alive!
Euphemia has betrayed us here!
All units, descend
upon the stadium!
Grind the Britannians to dust!
Damn you, Euphemia!
You deceived us!
[SOLDIER 1]
Damn Elevens!
Now I see.
You were planning
this all along!
[chattering, screaming]
[MAN 2]
Crush the Britannians!
[SUZAKU]
Euphy!
Euphy, where are you?!
[SUZAKU]
Get away from me...
I don't have time
to waste on you!
[LLOYD] Oh my, this is
turning into a mess.
How dare you... trampling over
the hopes of our people...!
Euphemia...!
[screaming]
[KALLEN]
Stop it!
[EUPHEMIA yelps]
Are you Japanese?!
You dare raise a hand against
Euphemia li Britannia?!
Huh?
A-ha, so there you are...
...you ridiculous royal puppet.
[EUPHEMIA] Oh! You were on
that island, weren't you?
[KALLEN]
Yeah.
Now suffer the hand
of vengeance--
--[ZERO] Wait.
--[KALLEN gasps]
[ZERO]
I'll deal with her.
You defiant Japanese!
[KALLEN]
Now what, Zero?
Do we take her prisoner?
There's no point.
Leave her.
I have to kill them all!
These Japanese people,
they have to die!
It jammed up! I have to--
Hurry!
I think it goes... in here.
[EUPHEMIA] Oh! I thought
you were one of them.
So, I was thinking we could run
the specially administrated
zone of Japan together...
Oh wait... Japan?
[ZERO]
Yes...
I would have liked that...
You and I, together.
[SUZAKU gasps]
Euphy...
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
Lelouch...
Why...?
[LELOUCH]
Farewell, Euphy.
You may have been the
first girl I ever loved.
[SUZAKU]
No...!
--[ZERO] Suzaku?!
--Why now of all times?!
[SUZAKU grunts] I'm no match
for that Hadron Cannon!
I will never allow
you to kill Lelouch!
--Suzaku!
--Get outta my way!
Ahh, dammit!
--[LLOYD grunts]
--[CECILE gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Please...
You have to save Euphy...
Do something! You
mustn't let her die!
[CORNELIA] You still haven't
made contact with Darlton?!
[SOLDIER]
No, Your Highness.
There was a report
he'd been injured,
but nothing beyond that.
[GUILFORD]
Viceroy!
Emergency message
from the Avalon!
[CORNELIA]
From the Avalon?
[GUILFORD]
Yes.
The special zone at Fuji has
fallen to the Black Knights.
What was that?!
[GUILFORD] They're moving
to intercept our forces.
Also...
Princess Euphemia...
[TAMAKI]
"Equality"?!
You can shove that straight
up your administrative ass!
You lured us into a death trap!
You just made the biggest
mistake of your lives!
You got that?!
--[MOB 1] That's right!
--[MOB 2] Let Britannia burn!
[MOB 3]
Don't screw with the Japanese!
[RAKSHATA]
Lucked out, didn't we?
I can't believe they left
all this footage
and equipment behind.
[DIETHARD]
Yes, once we're done editing,
we can throw it on the net
for the entire world to see.
It's pretty clear which
side justice is on.
[RAKSHATA]
How curious...
You don't feel any loyalty
toward Britannia, do you?
[DIETHARD]
Loyalty?
[RAKSHATA]
Mm-hm.
Btitannia's glory has
ripened on the vine.
My talents are
wasted serving them.
[giggles] You're
more of an honest man
than I thought you were.
[DIETHARD]
And what will you do now?
Hard to say...
The only reason I came
here was to gather data.
But I'd feel bad
abandoning you all.
And I find Zero so... amusing.
How wonderful to
finally meet you!
[ZERO]
This girl...
...she's a relative of Suzaku's.
Zero...
Are you prepared to work
beside us in what's to come?
--[ZERO] The opposite!
--[KIRIHARA, OHGI gasp]
[ZERO]
From this point on,
the six houses of Kyoto
will be under my control.
I won't hear any objections.
All other paths of
survival for you...
[KIRIHARA gasps]
[ZERO]
...have now vanished!
We should inform
Viceroy Cornelia...
Don't worry, I'll be
taking care of that.
Will she last until
we reach the bureau?
[DOCTOR]
I'm afraid not.
I'll contact Prince
Schneizel, then.
Excuse me.
[SUZAKU sobs]
[EUPHEMIA]
Suzaku...
[SUZAKU]
Euphy!
Euphy...
I have to know...
Why did you issue that
order at the stadium?
Order...?
What are you talking about?
[SUZAKU gasps]
Never mind that...
Suzaku...
You're Japanese, aren't you...?
[SUZAKU]
Y-Yeah...?
Euphy!
--[EUPHEMIA] No...
--Huh?
[EUPHEMIA]
I mustn't...
I-I can't even
think such a thing!
Oh, please...!
Suzaku?
Yes, Euphy?
[EUPHEMIA]
The ceremony...
Did it go all right?
Is Japan okay?
Euphy...
Don't you remember?
[cheering]
[ZERO]
People of Japan!
And all who are oppressed
by the Empire of Britannia!
Long have I waited...
All through the struggles
against Britannia's injustices,
I've waited for them to
come to their senses!
But that hope was betrayed...
...by an act of barbarism that
can only be called genocide!
How about everyone
that was there?
Are the Japanese happy?
--[MOB 2] Never forgive you!
--[MOB 4] She's a murderer!
--She's a filthy witch!
--Liar!
[yelling]
[ZERO] Euphemia is the symbol
of Britannia's hypocrisy!
A murderer cloaked in
the flag of a nation!
How was the ceremony?
Do you think I did... okay?
I hope that bitch burns in hell!
We're finished with your lies!
Death to them all!
Euphy...
The special zone is...
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
A great success!
The Japanese people were
given back their home!
And you did it!
Oh, thank god...
[ZERO] I hereby declare our
independence from Britannia!
But don't take this to mean
the resurrection of
your fallen nation...
We will not turn back
the hands of time!
The new Japan
we go on to build...
shall be one broad
enough to accept
all peoples, histories,
and ideologies!
Where the strong shall
not reign over the weak!
And it shall be called the
United States of Japan!
He's done it! This is
the birth of a nation!
How... strange...
I can't see...
your face anymore...
[SUZAKU sobs]
Keep going... to school...
I had to stop... before I...
...before I had the
chance to finish...
Euphy, you can
still go yourself.
I know!
Why don't we go to
Ashford Academy together?
The student council
is so much fun!
Euphy...
You have to do it... for me...
...'kay?
Please, Euphy...
No, don't go!
Suzaku...
I'm so happy... that we...
[SUZAKU gasps]
[monitor beeps]
[CROWD chants]
Zero! Zero! Zero!
[CORNELIA]
Dear god...
[LOUDSPEAKER]
Area Fukushima, Byakko squad,
en route to Ibaraki.
Area Tama, continuing with
barricade construction.
[C.C.] You plan to assault
the Tokyo settlement?
[ZERO]
Yes.
This is the best
chance we'll get.
Don't worry about it.
Your Geass has no effect on me.
You know that, don't you?
That's true, isn't it?
Hmph. With the Geass
out of control now,
I can never see anyone.
[phone rings]
Yes, Nunnally?
[NUNNALLY]
Hi, Lelouch!
I was wondering... um...
...do you suppose I could
talk to Euphy again?
[LELOUCH gasps]
I was thinking the three of us
could go to the school
festival together.
You see, Milly said they
were organizing another one,
since everything got all
messed up the other day.
So I was hoping we could go
to the new one together, too.
Oh... I'm sorry.
I know you don't want
us meeting ever again.
But I thought maybe,
if there was some way
you and I could maybe see
her just one last time--
Nunnally... Haven't
you heard the news?
Oh, well the radio cut
off mid-broadcast earlier.
Why do you ask,
did something happen?
Of course not.
Everything is just fine.
Sorry.
I'll be home by tomorrow.
We'll discuss it when I'm back.
--Right.
--[beep]
All right, so you can't
switch off your Geass.
Are there other changes
you've noticed?
[LELOUCH]
Not really. It's just...
Euphy...
She tried to resist the Geass...
...and my orders.
I was wondering if my
power had weakened.
But I think...
I think such a
malignant command...
...was simply
against her nature.
[C.C.]
And so?
I guess, that's all.
I-It was something...!
We have our contract.
I promise to stay with you...
...till the very end.
[STAFF A]
We weren't fast enough!
We may have managed to keep
the news off the net, but...
There's insurrections
all over the map!
[STAFF C]
That's correct!
The Black Knights are the
largest of the insurgent groups.
They are now absorbing
all of the masses
and advancing on the
Tokyo settlement!
[STAFF A] All our units
are in play right now,
we're completely on our own!
Yes, and with so many Honorary
Britannians turning on us,
our enemies number in
the tens of thousands!
[STAFF A]
Lord Guilford!
Forget it.
We cannot move without
Her Highness's word.
But sir!
The viceroy's been shut up
in Princess Euphemia's room
ever since she canceled
the attack orders!
[STAFF B]
And we still can't confirm
General Dalton's whereabouts!
[GUILFORD growls]
[NINA gasping]
[screams]
[RADIO 1] Everyone in Toyama
Squad is at your disposal.
[RADIO 2]
Roger that. Any weaponry?
[RADIO 1]
Some explosives from Gokayama.
But we don't have
enough vehicles.
Can any of us ride with you?
[RADIO 2] Best we can
offer are freight trains.
That okay?
Looks like the groups from
Yamanashi joined up with us.
Yeah, and the remnants of the
"Blood of the Samurai"
faction, too.
Our numbers are
growing by the minute!
[KALLEN] I hope everyone in the
student council can get away.
[C.C.]
On the contrary...
For the first time
in a while, I'm glad.
Yes...
I forgot the art of kindness
ages ago... Marianne.
[MAN A]
You worthless Brits!
[VILETTA] I hope you're
all right, Kaname.
You're working in
Shizuoka now, right?
[OHGI]
Yeah, I'm fine over here.
Look, Chigusa...
We need to talk about something
important when I get back.
[VILETTA gasps]
What's wrong?
Well, that's the first time
you've called me by that name.
[OHGI]
Oh, you're right.
Does it sound weird?
Not a bit!
Anyway, I'll be here.
--[banging]
--[gasps]
[MAN 1]
There she is! That Brit woman!
[MAN 2] Watchin' us
from your window, huh?!
Admit it, you're
some sort of spy!
[VILETTA gasps]
[NEWS MAN]
As the insurgents draw closer,
security in the ghettos
continues to worsen.
The government is
asking all citizens
to stay in their homes
until further notice.
Do you think the fighting
will come our way as well?
O-Of course not!
Princess Cornelia has her
regular forces stationed here!
There's no way!
[SHIRLEY]
I hope so.
Jeez, buck up, will ya?
You're scaring me.
Ah, Nunnally, what about
Lelouch, is he back here yet?
Lelouch?
Is something the matter?
No, not really...
Man... I wish you'd go
back to calling him Lulu.
It's time you two made up.
Lulu?
What, you mean
I called him that?
[RIVALZ]
Oh, there you go again...
Lulu...
[MILLY] Nina, they want
us upstairs in school.
The insurgents are
headed toward Tokyo!
Right. And Zero is
coming, isn't he?
[MILLY gasps]
[NINA] Please... Wait for
me, Princess Euphemia.
I'll avenge you, I swear!
[SUZAKU]
Euphy...
I just don't understand.
Why did you give that order?!
[V.V.]
Shall I tell you?
[SUZAKU gasps]
Huh? A child?
How did you get on board?
How do you do, Suzaku Kururugi?
You may call me V.V.
V.V.?
[STAFF GREY] They've broken
the Atsugi line, as well!
Maybe the homeland can help us!
They'll never make it in time!
Then we should evacuate
this area right away--
[CORNELIA]
Don't panic!
--[STAFF] Huh?
--[GUILFORD gasps]
P-Princess Cornelia!
[CORNELIA] I've put the
Glaston Knights on standby.
Place all our forces on
the outskirts of Tokyo!
We can end this!
We just need to take down Zero!
[ZERO] Kill Cornelia,
and the day will be ours!
You all have your orders.
Now be ready!
[ZERO] Diethard, have
Tohdoh handle the front line.
I'm leaving you in charge here.
Yes, very well, Zero.
[ZERO]
You're Sumeragi's--
Thank goodness,
I made it in time!
That was so mean of you,
the way you headed off
to battle without me.
I've been a huge fan of yours
ever since your big debut!
I was hoping that I'd
finally get to talk to you.
Wow! You're really
tall, aren't you?
Don't worry though!
I'll catch up with
you pretty soon!
L-Lady Kaguya...
I thought the heads of the
Six Houses remained in Fuji.
I followed after you!
So I could watch my
future husband fight.
[DIETHARD, C.C.]
Huh?
[ZERO]
Don't joke around.
Well, once you win this battle,
you'll eventually need
a wife, won't you?
I mean, I know your identity
is a big secret and all,
but you're gonna need somebody
as your public face, right?
[ZERO]
Really?
You believe we're going
to win this battle?
Of course!
I am the goddess of
victory after all!
[ZERO] I'd be lucky
to have you then.
Unfortunately, I've already
made a contract with the devil.
Huh?
[ZERO] I have no room in my
life for deities right now.
Hurry! We have to get
this experimental subject
back to the Homeland!
[RESEARCHER C]
The pressure!
The internal pressure is rising!
[RESEARCHER C, BARTLEY scream]
And now of all times...
Good morning to you, it was.
[ZERO]
Hear me, Britannia!
This is Zero!
A rebel against oppressors
who abuse their power!
We will wait until midnight.
You have till then
to surrender to me.
This is your only warning.
Heed it.
Twelve midnight, not
a single second later.
[DALTON groaning]
[T4 PILOT]
General Dalton,
you're in no
condition to do this!
I don't care, I have to be...
at her Highness's side...!
Your little bluff is
meaningless, Zero.
The Tokyo settlement is
an impenetrable fortress.
[C.C.] You can still
turn back, you know.
Your actions here will affect
more than just Area 11.
You... and this entire world...
will be steeped in war.
I'm aware of that.
And yet, all the same--
[phone rings]
[LELOUCH gasps]
Euphy? How could
that be possible?!
[LELOUCH]
No, it must be an imposter.
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch, it's me.
Suzaku.
Why are you calling me now?
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch...
Are you at the school?
[LELOUCH]
No, but I will be soon.
[SUZAKU]
I see.
I called because
there's something
I want you to tell
everyone for me.
[LELOUCH]
Yes, and what would that be?
[SUZAKU]
The sky...
Make sure no one
looks up at the sky.
[LELOUCH]
What?
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch...
Is there anyone you
could ever hate so much
that you'd actually
want to kill them?
There is, yes.
I used to feel that sort of
thinking was unacceptable.
That unless you
followed the rules,
killing someone was just murder.
But now...
It's hatred that's guiding me.
I'm fighting to kill someone.
[SUZAKU] I'm going to become a
murderer in the skies of Tokyo.
So please--
--[LELOUCH] Embrace your hate.
--[SUZAKU gasps]
Just think of Euphy.
I made my own mind up long ago.
I have no intention
of turning back.
[SUZAKU]
For Nunnally, you mean?
Yes...
I have to go now.
[SUZAKU]
Thank you, Lelouch.
Forget about it.
I mean, you and I
are friends after all.
[SUZAKU]
For the last seven years.
Right. See ya, then.
[SUZAKU]
Yeah. Later.
What the hell?!
These hands of mine
have been dirty
for a long time now, Suzaku.
You're coming to face me
now doesn't matter at all.
Hell, I welcome it even.
I mean, of course,
you and I are friends.
[chuckles]
[laughing]
Perhaps this is what
I've longed for...
...ever since that day.
The destruction and
loss of everything.
That's right.
Destruction always
comes before creation.
And for that goal, even my own
conscience must be cast aside.
The only path left to me
is straight ahead.
Now then...
[LELOUCH]
That's right.
Only by pushing forward
will I find atonement.
Even if my enemy is the
greatest empire on the planet,
there's no turning
back for me now!
Everything is in place...
The time has come to overthrow
the old world order!