[NARRATOR]
The date was August 10
in the year 2010 of
the Imperial calendar.
The Holy Britannian Empire had
just declared war upon Japan.
Confronted by Britannia's
newest weapon,
the formidable Knightmare Frame,
Japan fell to its enemy
in less than a month.
The conquered
nation was stripped
of its freedom, rights,
culture, and dignity.
Finally, even its name
was taken away.
Eleven.
The name of Japan and its people
was replaced with a mere number.
[LELOUCH]
I don't understand
what it is you wanted me to do?
Why did you give me
this bizarre power?
[explosion]
[LELOUCH gasps]
[gasps]
How could all these
royal guard be dead?!
[VILLETTA]
What happened here, boy?!
And why is a Britannian student
in a place like this?!
Are you deaf?!
Answer me, or I'll--
[grunts]
[VILLETTA]
Answer me!
I order you to
come out! At once!
Who the hell do you
think you are to order me?
[LELOUCH]
I see.
It only works with
direct eye contact.
[LELOUCH]
My name is Alan Spacer.
My father's a duke.
Nobility.
[LELOUCH] My I.D. card's
in my breast pocket.
After you confirm who I am,
I'll request your protection.
[VILLETTA]
Keep your hands up in the air.
I'll take out your I.D.
Now then, hand your
Knightmare over to me.
Understood.
The code number is XG21G2D4.
Got it.
[gasps]
What the--?
So, are we having a bad day?!
[SUZAKU]
Uh.
[LLOYD]
Looks like you missed a chance
to go heaven, Private Kururugi.
[SUZAKU]
I did? Uh.
Where...?
[LLOYD]
Hm? Ah.
We're still in
the Shinjuku ghetto.
[CECILE]
With Prince Clovis nearby,
this is probably the
safest place anywhere.
This is what saved
your life, Mr. Suzaku.
You're lucky it was
under your protective suit
because that's what
deflected the bullet.
Is it a keepsake?
Yeah. Very.
[LLOYD] You Elevens believe that
gods live inside of everything,
even objects, don't you?
I guess this one--
Is Lelou--?
What's the latest
on the situation?
[LLOYD] It looks like the
poison gas was released.
Massive Eleven casualties
have been reported.
[CECILE] They haven't caught
the perpetrators yet.
They haven't, huh? Not yet...
[LLOYD]
Private Kururugi,
how much experience do you have
in piloting a Knightmare Frame?
[SUZAKU]
Wha--?
But... there's no way an Eleven
would be made a knight.
Well, supposing you could.
Congratulations!
The only Knightmare
of its kind awaits you!
Once you take the controls
of this big beauty,
everything will change.
You and your world.
[CECILE]
Whether you want it to or not.
Those damned Brittanians!
[OHGI] Kallen! Can
the Glasgow still move?!
Don't worry, Ohgi, it's
all right! I'll decoy them!
Get the people out of here!
The only ones
that'll be captured
are those us in the resistance!
I know, but we're trapped!
They've got us
completely surrounded!
[TV AUDIENCE laughing]
[BOB] When that happens,
use this sticker.
[JACK]
What's that for?
[GIRL 1] That's because you
don't have enough leg strength,
right?
[GIRL 2] You're wrong.
You sink when you get fat.
[GIRL 3]
Because you snack, right?
--[phone ringing]
--[SHIRLEY] Huh?
[SHIRLEY]
Uh, Lelou?
Uh, what in the world
have you been doing?
Where are you now?
If you keep cutting class,
you'll get held back.
[LELOUCH]
Are you near a TV?
[SHIRLEY]
A TV?
[LELOUCH]
Sorry, but this is important.
[SHIRLEY]
Hmph.
Hang on.
Hey, can I change the channel?
[GIRL 1]
Huh? To what?
[LELOUCH]
The news.
Is there anything
about Shinjuku?
[SHIRLEY]
News? Let's see...
There's nothing on.
Traffic restrictions?
[LELOUCH]
Why is it restricted?
[SHIRLEY]
I dunno. They're not saying.
[LELOUCH]
I get it.
Once they finish everything off,
they'll release news
that favors the military.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[SHIRLEY] Oh, you're
gambling again, aren't you?
I've warned you before,
more than once,
how dangerous that is!
Yup. You caught me.
By the way,
tell my little sister that
I'm gonna be home late tonight,
would you? Thanks.
[SHIRLEY]
Oh!
Why does he always
hang up on me like that?!
[OPERATOR] The number you have
called is beyond service range.
Oh, darn it, not this again.
[LELOUCH] They need to keep
a lid on this information,
so it'll be hard for them
to call in reinforcements.
They'll have to make do with the
pieces they have on the board.
But I'm hemmed in here,
it'll be tough to break
through by myself.
Gaining refuge carries
its own risk, too.
[LELOUCH] I want payback for
bein' dragged into your fight.
[gasps]
It's our Glasgow friend.
Just 30 minutes left!
[LELOUCH]
The west entrance!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] Use the tracks
to move to the west entrance!
Who's this?!
How do you know this code?!
That doesn't matter!
If you wanna win, you're
just gonna have to trust me!
To win?
Okay, what am I
supposed to do now?
You pathetic Eleven.
If you simply run away,
this hunt hasn't much to
offer in the way of sport.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] Since you trusted
me, you're gonna win.
Jump onto the train!
[KALLEN]
Gotcha!
[JEREMIAH] You think you can
get through that way, hm?
If that's your plan, then...
You, go after the Glasgow!
[SOLDIER A]
Yes, my lord!
What the--?!
Shot by friendly fire?!
What's your name and your unit?!
We're after the one-armed Glas--
Oh my god! A terrorist?!
[JEREMIAH]
You son of a--!
[KALLEN yelling]
You saved me.
But how did you get a hold
of a Sutherland? Uh?
What? Where did he go?
[OHGI]
Kallen!
What the hell was that
radio message earlier?
[KALLEN]
What? He contacted you, too?!
Sure did. And Yoshida's
group oughta be here soon.
Hm?
[LELOUCH]
Are you in charge?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
[LELOUCH] I present to you the
cargo in that train over there.
They're tools for your victory.
If you want to use them to win,
then follow my orders.
[IGAMI]
There's more in here!
[TAMAKI]
Here, too!
[SUGIYAMA]
Amazing!
Maybe we can give
this guy a chance!
[KALLEN]
All this...
But how...?
[LELOUCH]
Woman in the Glasgow.
Y-Yes!
[LELOUCH]
Stay where you are.
Your unit's gonna run
decoy, you got that?
[KALLEN]
Understood.
[LELOUCH]
Energy filler status?
[KALLEN]
About 15 minute's worth.
[LELOUCH]
Then recharge it.
In ten minutes, I'll contact you
with your next instructions.
[sighs]
This is wearing me out.
Regardless, I'll need
determination to succeed.
After all, I'm betting
my life in this game.
[BARTLEY] The terrorists are
mixed among the Eleven populace
and they're mounting a minor
resistance against us.
But they pose little threat
to our vastly superior army.
[CLOVIS]
We know that. Moving on...
[BARTLEY]
Understood, Your Highness.
The gas capsules will be--
[CLOVIS]
What the public thinks.
[BARTLEY] Yes. We'll keep
searching for her.
Either way, I want her
captured, dead or alive.
[TAMAKI] Hey, are you certain
about this whole thing?
They've all had their IFF's
removed. What if this is a trap?
[OHGI] The other side has
total advantage in this war.
They don't need
to set any traps!
All right, people, let's move!
Get to your assigned points--
[LELOUCH]
P-1, can you move?
It operates basically the
same as what you're used to.
[OHGI]
Can't you tell us who you are?
At least your name.
[LELOUCH]
I can't do that.
What if these signals
are being intercepted?
Any way, if Q-1 is on
schedule, enemy Sutherlands,
probably two of them, will
reach you in 23 seconds.
Shoot them through the wall.
Aah! He's outta his mind!
[OHGI] Everyone,
double-check your weapons.
What?! Are you serious?!
[OFFICER A]
Enemy spotted at point F-31.
A feint, eh? How pedestrian.
[BARTLEY] Tell Lazlo
squad to go straight in!
Have Eugen and Valerie
strike from the rear!
Three... two... one... Fire!
[EUGEN]
What?!
[OFFICER A] Sir Eugen
and Sir Valerie, both lost.
Huh? An ambush?
[LELOUCH chuckles]
[LELOUCH] An I.D. signal
can be a double-edged sword.
Besides, if the terrorists
follow the orders I issue,
my task at hand is
sure to be completed.
[LELOUCH] P-1, P-4, P-7,
move 100 meters to the right.
Fire your slash harkens
toward three o'clock.
You heard him!
Do what the voice says!
Damn, what else does
he want us to do?!
[LELOUCH]
P-5, ready?
[TAMAKI]
Agh! Quit callin' me that!
[SOLDIER 1]
They're using the same--
[OFFICER B]
The enemy's moving towards G-28!
Send Lazlo squad--
I mean Glaube squad!
This means... terrorists
have our military weaponry?
[OFFICER C]
Sir Glaube has ejected!
His unit's been lost!
Change our codes! They're
intercepting our transmission!
[OFFICER D] We already
have, sir! Four times!
[BARTLEY]
Do it again!!
[CLOVIS]
This failure is unacceptable!
Forgive me!
Good afternoon!
[BARTLEY]
What is it?!
We're in the middle
of an operation!
I'd say it's time to deploy
the ASEEC's special weapon.
We've no time for
this right now!
[LELOUCH]
R-2, fire anchor.
B-7, use U.N. ordnance.
N-Group, you'll
continue your advance.
[REBELS yelling]
[LAZLO SQUAD yelling]
[STAFF OFFICER A]
We just lost Lazlo squad!
So do it! We'll have to
bring up Quincy's squad!
My lord, that will
break the encirclement!
Now then. The enemy has
five options. Their move...
[CLOVIS]
Reinforce the breach
with some of the
units guarding me.
All we know for certain is
that enemy forces are here.
Who ordered them
to break formation?
[LELOUCH] Well, that's a more
stupid move than I expected.
You, Q-1, do you
have an area map?
Yes, I have a map
of the old town.
But it has no current landmarks.
[LELOUCH]
It'll do.
All right. Send in Bertz
and the others, too!
Mission number three now.
Concentrate our forces
there! Surround them!
Is everything prepared?
[CLOVIS] The enemy's main
force is that center dot.
Finish every one of them off!
[chuckles]
What?! Where's the enemy?!
With this, I call check.
[CLOVIS gasps]
[LELOUCH laughing]
My plan worked, didn't it?
I can do it! I can!
I can defeat Britannia!
[CLOVIS]
Who...?
Who in hell am I up against?!
What if... he's even
better than Tohdoh?!
[CLOVIS]
Lloyd!
[LLOYD]
Yes, Your Highness?
[CLOVIS]
Can it win?
Will your toy beat them?
[LLOYD]
Hmph.
My lord. Please be so kind
as to call it Lancelot.
[COMM 1]
Z-0-1 Lancelot, now activating.
Lancelot activating.
Releasing hatch.
Z-0-1 Lancelot,
stand by for activation.
Pallet extension, initiating.
[CECILE]
Did you read the manual?
[SUZAKU]
Pretty much.
[CECILE]
Well done.
You scored at the top of
the class in the simulator.
Hey, look, about what
you told me earlier--
[CECILE]
Huh?
Ah... It could be, but the
possibility is nearly zero.
[SUZAKU] But that means
there's still a chance, right?
[CECILE]
Yes, I'm afraid that's true.
Even so, you're not to
do anything reckless.
The new system is not outfitted
with an ejection mechanism.
[SUZAKU]
Okay. I understand, Miss Cecile.
That's it?
[CECILE] Yes. The advanced
weapon developed by us
in the Advanced Special
Envoy Engineering Corps.
Lancelot. The world's first 7th
generation Knightmare Frame.
[LLOYD]
Well, if you're ready, Suzaku,
shall we proceed with
the initial start-up?
Initial start-up now
proceeding from phase 20.
Equipping energy filler.
[MAN 1]
Confirm pre-start.
Energy filler now
at full output.
[MAN 1] Thirty seconds
to reach critical voltage.
[MAN 2] Core luminous, shifting
phase. Yggdrassil Drive...
[CECILE]
Initiating Devicer set up.
[WOMAN 1] Confirming entry
of devicer into Z-0-1.
Individual ID
registration, confirmed.
Confirm man-machine
interface, engaged.
[CECILE]
Yggdrassil resonance, confirmed.
Rejection response, weak.
Devicer stress response, weak.
All readings nominal.
So far, it's going per the data.
[MAN 1]
Status, all green.
Status of back-up
tactical bank, authorized.
Secondary confirmation given.
[SUZAKU]
Lancelot.
Activate M.E. boost!
[CECILE]
Lancelot... launch!
[LLOYD laughing]
Running full throttle
right out of the gate!
[SUZAKU]
Cooler than the manual.
With this-- Uh.
[TAMAKI]
Huh?
What is that?
It doesn't look like a Suther--
[LELOUCH chuckling]
[LELOUCH] Another push, and
the checkpoint with fall...
[TERRORIST 1] This is B-group,
reporting enemy presence!
[LELOUCH]
Hm? Reinforcements?
Real battle is
different, isn't it?
[LELOUCH]
Status.
[TERRORIST 1]
Everyone ejected,
but they took out four
units in nothing flat!
[LELOUCH]
Enemy numbers?
[TERRORIST 1]
Just one!
I think it's a new model.
Never seen anything like-- Ah!
[gasps] What's
happening out there?!
[TERRORIST 2]
Bastard!
What?! It reflects bullets?
[TERRORIST 2]
Ah! What do we do?!
Ishida!
[TERRORIST 2 screams]
[LELOUCH]
Useless so-called terrorists.
With all the
resources they have,
they're being
beaten by one unit.
[TERRORIST 3]
Dammit!
Yes, I can do this!
With Lancelot, I can
stop all this at once!
[LELOUCH]
N-4, N-5, hold there.
When the rear units arrive,
surround that thing!
[TERRORIST 4]
Gotcha.
[TERRORIST 5]
We can't stop it!
N-units, what is it?!
[static]
What happened?
Something I didn't foresee?
[CLOVIS]
For heaven's sake...
Now I'll owe my older brother
a debt I don't need to incur.
It's for the best, though.
[screaming]
[LELOUCH]
P-1, report!
The enemy...
Can it really be
only one unit?
These readings are even
higher than predicted.
It's because our pilot is
taking his job very seriously.
[SUZAKU] If I can stop
all of the Knightmares,
then this battle is over.
No matter what it takes,
I've gotta save Lelouch
and that girl.
Uh?
[gasps]
You mean this thing's
what's ruining my plan?!
Are you the guy
that's in command?
Nothing more than a
pilot! How dare he!
No choice, I've gotta
get outta here!
Hey! I'm returning the favor!
I can't--!
[LELOUCH]
I must remember that.
The most vital element
in battle is the human one.
--[phone ringing]
--[LELOUCH] Uh?!
That damn monster's unstoppable!
Bastard! He's tearing
things up for no reason!
--[phone ringing]
--[SUZAKU] Huh?
[WOMAN screaming]
[LELOUCH] In the midst of
battle, he rescues someone?
Hmph. I'll concede you
the tactical victory here.
Nevertheless...
Huh? He saved someone?
Yes. So it would seem.
[LLOYD]
Hmm...
It's very strange of him.
[WOMAN screaming]
[gasps]
[CECILE]
Suzaku?
Are you tired? We'll
call it quits for today.
[SUZAKU] No,I'm fine.
Please let me keep going.
[LLOYD] Be careful with
his operational time!
[CECILE]
Yes, sir!
[LLOYD] My, that boy's an
excellent piece of equipment.
[GUARD]
Stop there! Your I.D.
This is Prince Clovis'
personal transport!
[LELOUCH]
At last, the checkpoint.
And barely guarded, per my plan.
Your plan?
[LELOUCH]
That's right.
Now, I'd like you
to let me pass.
Yes, sir. Understood.
Kallen!
[ELEVEN MAN 1]
It's your fault!
This is what happens when
you oppose the Britannians!
[TAMAKI]
What?! Why, you gutless coward!
How many people were
killed because of this?!
Shut up! Do you know how many
of us were killed or captured?!
Do ya?!
Quit cryin'!
Ohgi, who was
that voice we heard?
[OHGI]
Damned if I know.
He doesn't answer when I call,
so maybe he bought it.
[gasps]
There, you see?!
Instead of following somebody
we don't even know,
we should've used
the poison gas!
But he--
Damn Nagata to hell!
[COMMANDER]
So, this is where
you Eleven vermin
scurried off to.
Prepare to fire!
Naoto!
Commence--
[CLOVIS] Attention, all forces!
Cease fire at once!
Uh?
[SUZAKU]
Cease fire?
[CLOVIS] I, Clovis,
third prince of Brittania,
and royal viceroy of Area 11,
hereby command you!
All forces are ordered
to cease fire at once!
You will also cease destruction
of any buildings or property!
All casualties, whether
Britannian or Eleven,
shall be treated equally
and without prejudice!
In the name of
Clovis La Britannia,
you are hereby ordered!
Cease fire at once!
I shall allow no
further fighting!
Are you satisfied?
[LELOUCH]
Very. Well done.
[CLOVIS]
And what shall we do now?
Sing a few lively ballads?
Or perhaps a nice
game of chess.
[LELOUCH]
That has a familiar ring.
[CLOVIS]
Hm?
[LELOUCH]
Don't you recall?
The two of us used to play
chess together as boys.
Of course, I would always win.
[CLOVIS]
What?
[LELOUCH]
Remember? At the Aries villa?
You...
Who are you?
[LELOUCH]
It's been a long time...
...big brother.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] The eldest son of
the late Consort Marianne
and 17th in line to
the imperial throne.
Lelouch vi Britannia,
at your service.
[CLOVIS]
Lelouch? But-But I thought--
[LELOUCH]
That I was dead? You were wrong.
I have returned, Your Highness.
And I've come back
to change everything.
[LELOUCH]
How could a single student
ever be able to
change the world?
It isn't realistic.
Just think about it for a
moment, and you'll see that.
Nevertheless...
Now that I hold the advantage...
...there may be a strategic
move I need to play.