[KNIGHT 12]
There was a giant explosion
in the Tokyo Settlement.
It appears that a F.L.E.I.J.A.
warhead caused it.
Your Majesty, should we
remain here at Kamine Island?
Enough! Let Schneizel
handle mundane affairs.
[NEWSMAN A] At least
ten million inhabitants
are believed dead from the
initial impact of the blast.
[NEWSMAN B] Secondary damages
might have caused 25 million
more casualties. All rescue
facilities were wiped out,
so we cannot care for
any of the wounded.
[NEWSMAN C] The Tokyo
settlement is now no more.
No. How could this
have happened?
They're all They're all...!
I did it?! I did this?
[GINO] The school was outside
the blast radius. But...
This has gone beyond war.
[TOHDOH]
If they use this weapon again,
the Black Knights will
be completely wiped out!
[ZERO]
Tohdoh, it's me.
Zero, we can't remain--
[ZERO] Have all forces
land in the Tokyo settlement.
Search for Nunnally.
Wait a minute!
We've lost Asahina!
And we have massive casualties!
[ZERO]
You think I care about that?!
[TOHDOH]
Uh?!
Find Nunnally now!
That's an order!
All forces search for Nunnally!
[TOHDOH]
What's happened to Zero?!
[OHGI] The fugitives on the
portside runway, right?
[FUTABA] Wait! We need to
reorganize our forces first!
[OHGI] Understood! I'll be
back there in a minute!
[VILLETTA]
Ohgi!
[OHGI]
Uh?
Chigusa.
[DIETHARD] That's far enough!
Miss fugitive.
[gasps]
[DIETHARD] Cornelia?! I thought
it was Villetta who'd escaped.
So it's you.
Newsman and turncoat.
[DIETHARD]
Is Zero behind this?
Secretly holding the
princess as a captive?
He should have shown a
little more trust in me.
Aim for her legs!
I want her taken alive, men!
[MEN]
Yes, sir!
[siren wails]
[RADIO GUY] Attention! We
are carrying a Britannian
special envoy on an urgent
diplomatic mission!
We have no hostile intentions!
Diplomatic mission? Minase,
was that craft cleared
to land through
official channels?
Schneizel!
Impossible!
Why would he step right into
the midst of his mortal enemies?
[LELOUCH] Tohdoh!
I told you to find Nunnally!
Now deploy the search teams!
Kallen, do you hear me?
Rolo! Jeremiah!
Nunnally has to be alive!
Find her! Find Nunnally!
[TOHDOH]
Attention, all forces!
Fall back to Makuhari
and reform our battle line!
All forces, fall back now!
Tohdoh! I told you to
search for Nunnally!
[gasps]
As long as my brother is safe...
..then we will have
another chance.
[XING-KE] Why have they called
a temporary cease fire?
What are the Britannians up to?!
Why did Bismarck withdraw?!
[XIANG-LIN]
We're trying to find that out,
but they don't seem to
be preparing a new attack.
And there's a cease
fire in Tokyo, as well.
Did Zero order it?
[C.C.]
Uh? Master, you're back! Uh!
Hang in there, big brother.
[LELOUCH]
Nunnally...
[ROLO]
Big brother, I'm here for you...
We've been doing fine with just
the two of us, haven't we?
[phone rings]
[ROLO] Jeremiah?
Please give my brother some
time right now.
You can talk to him later.
Right. It may not mean
much of anything. Mm.
After all, I'm here with him.
[LELOUCH gasps]
What are you doing with
this?! It's Nunnally's!
I wanted to give this locket
to Nunnally, not to you!
To Nunnally!
You think you could ever
replace Nunnally in my heart?!
You're an imposter!
[ROLO, C.C.]
Uh!
Haven't you figured
it out yet? I hate you.
I loathe you. I despise you!
I've been trying to kill you,
but I just keep
missing the chance!
[ROLO]
Big brother...?
[LELOUCH]
Get out of here!
I never want to see
your face again!
I said get out!
[ROLO whimpers]
[NINA] I didn't understand
what this kind of destruction
really means. It was all
just numbers. But now...
[LLOYD] You need to
make a choice, Nina.
Do you abandon science
to preserve your heart,
or abandon your heart and
sacrifice yourself to science?
How can I do either?
Did you make such a
choice, professor Lloyd?
[LLOYD] I didn't have to,
I'm a sociopath.
I was born with an
abandoned heart.
But I'm the one who built
the F.L.E.I.J.A warhead.
All those people's lives
are gone. I killed them!
All of them!
[CHIBA]
It's no use. There's no answer.
[DIETHARD]
We don't have any choice, then.
We'll have to meet Prince
Schneizel without Zero.
[RAKSHATA] But, Zero's
our leader, after all.
Should we be making
decisions without him?
It was a massacre! They
killed everyone, including
women and children! Kinoshita
said it was Zero's orders!
[CHIBA]
Diethard!
[CHIBA] Why didn't you
take Schneizel captive?
We could've avenged Asahina.
He only has one
Knightmare guarding him.
Because they came equipped
with a massive
F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
F.L.E.I.J.A.?
[DIETHARD] Like the one
that just destroyed
the Tokyo settlement.
It's a new weapon.
If they unleash it, it will kill
us and Zero in a heartbeat.
We don't know what
Schneizel's objective here is.
So our best option is to
meet with him and find out.
[RAKSHATA]
I think, I'll pass.
I want to system-check my
Guren now that it's back.
Then the negotiators
will be myself,
Chiba, Diethard, as well as--
[TAMAKI] Forget it.
I can't find Ohgi anywhere.
Dammit! Where'd
that fool go, huh?
[MINAMI]
Kallen!
Thank goodness, you're
back in one piece!
Sorry to worry you, I'm okay.
Uh, where's Zero?
I heard he's in his quarters.
There's a rumor that
he was wounded.
Lady Nunnally, I pray you're
still alive. Fervently.
[CORNELIA]
That's all,
everything I saw and
heard at the Order.
[SCHNEIZEL] Thank you, Cornelia.
With this information, I can--
[DIETHARD]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[TAMAKI] Yeah, Sorry.
We've had our hands full
with all the ten million dead
people you guys slaughtered.
Tamaki, we discussed
this already.
You can't be here for this.
Why not? I'm the
Black Knight's Interior
Custodian Minister so I can
sit in for my bud, Ohgi,
and fill him in later!
[DIETHARD] You're the only
one who has that impression.
[SCHNEIZEL]
No...
Please. I'd like for
him to join us, as well.
[DIETHARD]
Huh?
[SCHNEIZEL]
Shin'ichiro Tamaki.
As Zero's oldest comrade,
you are the brave veteran
of many historic battles.
[TAMAKI]
Ha! You all know about me, huh!
[DIETHARD]
T-Tamaki! Please.
[JEREMIAH] You rescued me a
long time ago, didn't you?
Very courageous.
I came here to thank you for
that honorable act. Indeed...
You and I share a
rather odd connection,
don't you think?
I suppose it's fate that we
became enemies in the end.
I'll take my leave now, sir. I
must search for Lady Nunnally.
Nunnally's dead. She's gone.
[CLAUDIO] Survivors are
directed to register in order.
Along with your I.D. number,
give your name, age, address,
and blood type. If you
require medical attention,
please go to the medical
information desk
and take a number.
To minimize disorder, please...
[RIVALZ screams]
Rivalz!
Oh, Prez, just tell
me you're alive.
Yes. I am. I'm alive!
[RIVALZ]
Thank goodness!
[MILLY]
You can say that again!
[RIVALZ, MILLY laugh]
[SCHNEIZEL]
Now that I think of it,
I never finished my
match with Zero, did I?
Zero won't be attending.
Not until we have the
details of the proposal.
[SCHNEIZEL] Of course.
I didn't expect him to show up.
[DIETHARD]
Hm?
[SCHNEIZEL] He's not the type
who consults with others.
No, he keeps things to himself
and holds people at a distance.
[DIETHARD]
That's strange,
you talk about him as if
you know him intimately.
[SCHNEIZEL]
More than any of you do.
[ALL gasp]
Zero is our younger brother.
Cornelia's and my own.
Huh?
What are you saying?!
He is the former
11th royal prince
of the Holy Britannian Empire:
Lelouch vi Britannia.
The man whom I both loved and
feared more than any other.
Impossible!
You're telling us that Zero's
a Britannian prince?!
Diethard, please
in all this time,
you never figured that out?
Even with all the information
you were getting from
Jeremiah and Villetta?
[TAMAKI exhales]
[DIETHARD] You're wasting your
time. You can't cause chaos
here by spreading
these irrelevant stories.
It's not Zero's lineage that
matters, but rather his efforts
and the miracles that
he's performed for us.
But, what if all those
miracles he performed
were actually tricks?
[DIETHARD]
Tricks?
Zero possesses a special power.
It is known as Geass.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SCHNEIZEL] It's the absolute
power to compel anyone
to obey him. You can think
of it as extreme hypnosis.
You're saying his miracles
come from that power?
Are you tryin' to
dis my man Zero?
He's got brains and guts
and he kicks Britannian butt!
A prince with Geass power!
Where's the proof of
all this bull, huh?
[OHGI]
I have the proof!
[TAMAKI]
Ohgi.
[CORNELIA]
And Villetta?
What he's saying is all true.
Zero is a former Britannian
prince named Lelouch.
He controls people
with his Geass power.
A con man!
[OHGI] Zero's been
tricking us all along!
Using us like pawns,
from the start!
[TAMAKI]
You don't mean this, Ohgi.
[CHIBA] But, if that's
really true, then...
[DIETHARD]
Then it doesn't matter!
It doesn't erase a single thing
that he's done for us.
And if he really does
have this Geass power,
then doesn't that just help us?
It's another weapon to use in
our fight against Britannia.
Yes, that would
make perfect sense
if he only used it
against our enemies!
[TAMAKI]
What?
[CHIBA] Are you saying
he used it on us?
Of course.
He used geass to control
his own sister, Euphemia.
He made her slaughter the
Elevens in the Special Zone!
You're lying. Zero's
a knight for Justice!
He would never do
something like--
We have evidence.
[SUZAKU] Did you use your Geass
Power on Euphy? Be honest.
[LELOUCH]
Yes.
[SUZAKU] You caused her
massacre the Japanese?
[LELOUCH]
I ordered her to do it.
Then, that whole
bloodbath was...
Euphy was just a girl.
Zero was in control.
So Zero slaughtered our people
for his own ambitions?!
That recording is fake!
These are people and incidents
that we suspect he manipulated,
with his Geass.
[gasps] Kusakabe.
Even Major General Katase.
[CHIBA]
I can't... believe it.
[DIETHARD]
Clovis...
[VILLETTA]
He used it on me, too.
[DIETHARD]
Hm?
[OHGI] That explains
why Gao-Hai changed.
[VILLETTA]
And it explains why
Jeremiah and the others
became traitors.
His Geass might be
controlling even me now.
There's no way to be
certain about that.
When you think about it,
it's a terrifying prospect.
You mean...?!
We could be...?!
[KANON] There's one more
thing. We notified Zero
about the F.L.E.I.J.A.
warhead before the battle.
We wanted to avoid using it.
It's still in the Lancelot's
communications record.
However...
He never told us
anything about that.
We can't trust
Commander Zero!
[TOHDOH]
Asahina...
I wanted to put
my trust in Zero!
I wanted to believe in him!
But we mean nothing to him,
we're just pawns.
Treating us like chumps?! Damn!
How could he do this to us?!
[yells]
Everyone, Zero is my brother.
Will you please hand him
over to me for justice?
[TAMAKI cries]
On one condition.
[ALL gasp]
[TAMAKI]
Ohgi!
You think you're in a position
to bargain over this?!
Wait, let's hear it.
Our Japan. Return it.
[ALL gasp]
[OHGI]
We're betraying our comrade.
So at least we deserve
to regain Japan.
Otherwise I could never
forgive myself.
[C.C.] Master, please
take off your clothes.
[LELOUCH grunts]
What?
Are you hurting somewhere?
If it's someplace you can't
reach, I can help.
[LELOUCH gasps, sighs]
[LELOUCH] That's right.
It's someplace I can't reach.
[KALLEN] Zero, are you there?
Can I come in?
It's me.
Is that Kallen?
[KALLEN] Ohgi asked me to
bring you to Warehouse Four.
[LELOUCH]
Why there?
[KALLEN]
Sorry, I didn't get the details.
[C.C.]
Master?
[KALLEN]
Uh?
Please take off your clothes.
I'll do the best
I can, I promise.
Uh! What the hell have the
two of you been doing here?!
While I've been
rotting in a cell y--!
[LELOUCH] No, you've got
it wrong. She was...
C.C. lost her memory.
[gasps]
It happened because of me.
So, the C.C. you knew is gone
now, erased, and it's my fault.
[gasps]
[KALLEN]
Her mind was erased?
[KALLEN] C.C.'s gone.
And Nunnally's been killed.
That means Lelouch is now...
[LELOUCH]
Kallen.
[KALLEN]
Uh!
[LELOUCH]
It's good you made it back.
I'm sorry it took so
long to get you out.
Lelouch, listen when
I was imprisoned,
I happened to talk to Nunnally.
She stood up for me
and she saved me.
[LELOUCH]
I see.
[KALLEN] Look, I'm not sure what
to say at a time like this...
But when I lost
my brother, I--
[KALLEN, LELOUCH gasp]
Surrender, Zero!
How dare you try to run
a con game on us!
We know everything
about your Geass power!
[LELOUCH gasps]
[DIETHARD]
"Zero, the renowned hero,
died in battle before
he could triumph.
But his gallant life
and daring deeds will
continue to live on
in myth and legend!"
[LELOUCH] Is that the script
you've written for me, Diethard?
Actually, I wanted to film
your brilliant campaign
and glorious victory
over Britannia,
but I'm afraid that show has
been permanently cancelled.
[LELOUCH]
What do I do?
Knightmares are
beyond my reach,
but Ohgi and the others
are defenseless!
If I can use my
Geass secretly...!
Everybody trusted you, Zero!
Inoue and Yoshida sacrificed
their lives for you!
Wait a minute!
This is all one-sided!
Look at how far we've
come because of Zero!
At least let him answer!
[TAMAKI]
You're in the way, Kallen!
[SUGIYAMA]
Do you want to die with Zero?!
[MINAMI] Don't tell me he
used his Geass on you, too!
I need an answer, Lelouch.
What do I mean to you?
I have to know.
[KALLEN] If I could stay
with you, I would... Please.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Schneizel. You made your move
and now you're calling check.
There's no way out of
this for me. It's over.
Please, answer me, Lelouch!
[LELOUCH laughs]
[KALLEN]
Uh!
[LELOUCH] Fools!
You finally figured it out!
That I've been using you all.
That's right. You're all
just pawns in my game!
Zero! So, you really are...
Zero!
Lelouch, no.
Kallen, you were my
most useful piece;
much like a well-played,
knight. This whole world
was the board for the game.
And all for my entertainment.
I see...
[KALLEN]
Goodbye then, Lelouch.
Get ready!
Kallen. You have to live.
[KALLEN gasps]
Fire!
[ALL gasp]
[ROLO]
Are you okay, brother?!
Rolo!
[TOHDOH] Never mind!
Open fire! Hit the Shinkiro!
Wait!
Big brother,
I'll protect you!
Stop it, Rolo!
You've done enough!
Uh!
Oh, my master...
Uh. They're gone!
The Shinkiro...!
Vanished. Just like
in Babel Tower...
Anya, Zero has escaped.
Can you capture him
with the Mordred?
I can only destroy it.
I never knew how hard it was
to calculate the Absolute
Defense Field.
My big brother really is
incredible, isn't he?
[LELOUCH] Rolo! I have no
reason to live anymore!
Huh?
Uh?
How can it move like that?
[ROLO] I won't let them
kill you! I swear it!
[LELOUCH] Using your Geass over
such a large area...
Rolo! I's way too much,
your heart can't take
that much strain!
[DIETHARD] Attention, all units!
The Shinkiro has been stolen!
Search out and
destroy the Shinkiro!
I Repeat, destroy the Shinkiro!
[ROLO, LELOUCH groaning]
That's enough, Rolo! I don't
want to live any more!
I won't stop, brother.
Because of this...
[LELOUCH]
Don't do--
All throughout my whole life,
people have used me like a tool.
...this, Rolo! Why are
you still trying--
[ROLO]
I was used by the Order...
...to save me?! You know that--
[ROLO] And then you
used me, big brother.
Uh. Yeah, Maybe
you've been using me
for your own ends right
from the very start...
But only the time I spent
with you seemed real.
...I was only usin--
[ROLO] It was those memories
that finally made me...
human!
[ROLO groaning, coughing]
...using you! Uh! Rolo!
That's why I'm not I'm not...!
[coughs] I'm not...
No, stop using your Geass like
that! Do you want to die?!
I'm not... a tool. I do this...
of my own... free will!
As a human being!
[LELOUCH] Rolo, why did you save
me? After all I've done to you?
[ROLO] Because you're
a liar, big brother.
[LELOUCH]
Uh.
[ROLO]
It was a lie, wasn't it?
What you said about
trying to kill me.
About hating me
and all of that.
Of course And you saw
right through me, didn't you?
Just what I'd expect
of my little brother.
That's right. I thought so...
'Cause I know who you really
are inside your heart...
I know everything about
you, big brother...
Yes, you got it right.
Your big brother is just a liar.
[RADIO GUY C]
We cannot locate the target.
[RADIO GUY D]
Increasing the search area.
[RADIO GUY E] Request to
send in ground units.
[SUZAKU laughs]
[LELOUCH]
Nunnally. Rolo. Shirley.
The Black Knights.
I've lost everything.
This is the result which
I've been left with.
No. It's my just punishment.
But now, thanks to this...
Thank you, Rolo.
You saved my life for a reason,
because there's still a task
that's waiting
for me out there.
Yes. Something
I have to finish...
[EMPEROR]
Who would've imagined
that I would ever happen
to use the system here.
The Ragnarok Connection.
So now, the old world
shall be destroyed,
and a new world shall
be created in its place!
[LELOUCH] My father,
Charles zi Britannia!
If I am on the road to hell,
then I'll take you with me.
This is my final
mission! I swear it!
[LELOUCH] Rolo. What was our
relationship, in the end?
[laughs]
It's strange to think that.
Even knowing the
truth, you still...
You of all people stuck by
me to the very last. Yeah...
I always realize these
things when it's too late.
To you, I wasn't Lelouch
vi Britannia, was I?
I was Lelouch Lamperouge,
your big brother.