Tamo No-Rin High School, Class 2-A Daily Journal.
Entry by Kousaku Hata.
Today was pretty typical, actually.
Nothing out of the ordinary. Same people, same routine.
Everybody just keeping on keeping on.
Kind of a yawn-fest, really.
I helped check out the cornstalks,
making sure that bugs or
disease weren't getting to them.
Ah... You need something, Yoshida?
Hey, what's up? I didn't know you were on corn duty.
Yeah. Me neither.
Not that it particularly matters,
but I wonder what you out-of-towners
are doing for summer break?
So far all we know is our training schedule.
W-What about Kamatori?
Is he going home? Sticking around?
I don't know.
One way to find out, though.
Hey, Kei!
Ugh! Dammit! Were you dropped on your head?!
Need something, Kousaku?
So what do you got lined up for this summer?
Probably stay on campus and work for a bit.
We should make a trip down to the beach, yeah?
You want to come with?
B... B... You idiot!
How dare you invite me to tag along all casual-like?
You've got some nerve!
So, you don't want to go on a beach trip with Kei?
Must we hold this conversation
out in the open for all to see?
You are an evil mastermind!
Or an idiot! I can't tell which!
Shh!
I don't hear any birds.
Or the livestock.
Something's coming. Kei, what is it?
Something... inhuman.
It's here!
It's a demon!
You like a boy?
Where's mine?!
Of course!
It was summoned by Yoshida's obvious love for Kei,
which I totally didn't mean to out, but whatever!
Huh? How's it my fault?!
Run for it, Youkul! Go!
Dude, his name's Jun...
Yoshida! Get the girls to school!
I'm on it!
Kei! Don't let the cougar-demon touch you, or game over!
Horny teacher! Calm your fury!
Whatever you may be, cougar or spinster loli,
these boys are not yours to devour!
Yeah, she ain't gonna like that.
Young love can suck it!
Are you all right, Kei?
Yeah!
She's heading for the campus!
The girls are in danger!
Ringo... no!
Are you okay?!
We'll never catch her!
Damn it!
Oh, Youkul!
Still not his name, bro.
Kei!
Yaaah!
All right!
You saved us all!
Goodness.
She didn't go down easy.
You showed her who's boss!
Yoshida, were you hurt? Are you okay?
Huh?! Of course I'm okay! Why would you even ask?
That's good. Glad to hear it.
Huh...?
Wait until your goods start migrating south,
Tits McGee. You'll know my suffering soon enough!
Whatever, Teach... you're just jelly.
So, yeah, corn duty was pretty dull.
And homeroom was same old, same old.
Honestly, kind of...
...a bust.
Hey there, little lady.
So what caliber of ammo are you smuggling?
H-cup? Or I?
Damn, they're big.
Hey! Don't give them the third-degree!
But... I gots to know!
That's enough of that, fella!
"Fella?"
You think those sweater-puppies
can be kenneled in a cup-size?
That's like trying to store the Sahara in a litter-box!
Huh?
That said, if you want to think about
'em in terms of a cup size, they are...
World Cup boobs!
World Cup boobs?
Duh!
No one country can lay claim to such god-tier knockers!
Those watermelons are worldwide!
I'll pass!
Big boobs are nothing more than
oversized bags of bovine fat.
Really, they do nothing but hinder a woman.
Any busty girl will tell you so.
Yeah! A-cup forever, haters!
Seriously?!
Hey, Boss!
You want to drop some knowledge about the itty-bitties?
Don't call me "Boss".
Call me "Big Brother"!
What the hell?
Allow me to demolish his worldview.
Sure.
Men are creatures that wish
to be mothered on some level.
Nothing symbolizes that role as well, as the breast.
Ergo, huge breasts are the realm of the real man!
Says you.
What?!
The desire for mothering is a real phenomenon.
However... Any self-respecting guy should be well
out of that phase by high school.
As they break away from their parents
and become men in their own right,
a new desire starts to rear its head!
You're overlooking a biological directive!
What is it? Enlighten me, tiny schoolgirl!
Behold! Paternal instinct!
Say what?
As a boy grows into a man,
he awakens to a new paternal instinct within.
What use has he for teats?
Giving a little girl fatherly love
is the most natural of acts for a grown male!
Anything less is a case of arrested development!
Yay!
Higher, big brother!
Having fun?
Uh-huh! I love you, big brother!
I admit. Such a scenario is appealing.
Yikes...
So, what size do you like?
Huh? Boob-wise?
Mmm...
You know, boobs are nice and
all, but at the end of the day,
I'm more of a foot guy, really.
Huh?
Yeah.
Like the soles of a girl who's wearing black knee-highs.
Or maybe she's been clomping around in shoes all day,
and now they're, you know... musty...
Are you having fun?
Why, yes... Yes I would
like to rub them for you!
'Sup, guys! How's it hangin'?
C'mon! That was totes adorbs!
You're over forty!
How come you're so mean to me? Boo-hoo!
I'm trying to be as young and lively as possible!
You've got to respect that!
No, we don't! You look ridiculous!
Better to be ridiculous than dead!
My Gaia... Burn them with moe!
She's so powerful!
How could a woman her age be so strong?
In a world where couples are running amok,
she appears to punish us for their happiness!
She fights with the force of a thousand ignored
online-dating profiles!
She rises from the ashes of her own
wreck of a love-life again and again!
She is the perpetually-single Phoenix!
Run, you fools! Get out of here!
Wrong Side of Forty.
Genma. Fist!
Birth.
Kindergarten.
Elementary school.
Middle school.
High school.
College.
Work.
Suddenly, I was forty...
...and just as friggin' lonely as ever...
Even my 13-year-old niece has a boyfriend.
Seriously, life, what the actual hell?
Holy crap!
Wrinkles! The wrinkles are everywhere!
My boobs will be down to my feet!
Going out to eat, and every single time
it's the same thing: "Becky, party of one!"
The future... it really sucks!
I never knew that being an adult was so horrible!
It's nothing but loneliness!
Day after day, a never-ending parade of suck!
We'd all be better off dead!
That took the piss outta ya, huh?!
Now, who loves Becky?
Me.
The afternoon class was Home Ec.
"If you make something good to eat...
...you'll have 'em lined up down the street."
It's Kousaku's...
...and Ringo's...
...cooking show! "Let's Go Home Ec!"
Hey, everybody, you know what time it is.
Let's bring out our guest instructor for the day, yeah?
She was top of her class in culinary school,
and won the Worldwide Singles Cooking Contest
22 years in a row! You know her...
You love her...
...kind of...
It's Ms. Becky!
I say 40 is the new 18!
Well, Ms. Becky, you certainly seem glad to be here.
Is that a phone? Come on, you guys.
It's really distracting to
hear that in the middle of a...
Oh, my bad.
You want to answer it?
That is not a phone!
All-righty!
Today's dish is so good,
just one bite and any man will be yours forever!
Better eat up! This feline's got needs, Hata!
Me-Meow!
Kill me.
Put something in his mouth that he likes.
Maybe he'll return the favor! Know what I mean?
Hata, what do you like to eat?
I'm not really that picky, but...
I kind of draw the line at natto. I mean, it's so...
What the hell do you like to eat?!
It wasn't a hard question, was it?!
Time to shave the tuna, you guys!
Now...
Check it out. Skipjack.
No second-rate bonito for you guys.
Well, Ringo, how do you think it smells?
Like tuna, because it's tuna.
Aw, geez!
Stop the tape! Cut!
We got to take that react again.
Why'd we stop filming?
Oh, come on.
Check the mannequin for a pulse,
'cause that was crappy-crap.
I don't think color commentary is Ringo's forte.
If you think you can coast by on your fresh face
and thousand-yard-stare,
just sit your bony ass down already!
I don't think we need that for this recipe!
Yeah. Calm your tits.
Now, I'll show you how to prep
skipjack tuna the Ms. Becky way!
Oh, my... This thing has such a musky odor to it.
But I... kind of like it.
Wow. There's something on the tip!
Is that what I think it is, you naughty skipjack... ?
No, it's not!
I'm sorry.
I guess I got a little ahead of myself.
Get it? "A little head?"
Hey, Hata! Want to be a pal and shave this down?
Aw. I'm going to be sad to see you go, mister skipjack.
You're like a giant di...
Kousaku reporting in for shaving duty!
Shave, shave, shave...
Faster, faster!
Don't be so rough.
Shave... Shave...
Gimme a Latin beat!
Shave, sh-sha-shave
Right, now show me your O-face!
What is your problem?!
After that, you fill up a bowl with white rice!
Here. Knock yourself out.
Then, you grab a big bottle of sauce!
So what're we making here, anyway?
What the... ?
Rice bowl... voila! Loved up and good to go!
Isn't that a bit too simple for a cooking show?
Ah-ah-ah! There's no point going crazy in the kitchen
when you're the only one who's going to be eating
the final product, right?
Here's the reality.
On any given day, you just go from your
apartment to work and then back home again.
At work, your so-called peers
avoid you like the plague. And they somehow forget
to invite you to their parties every damn time.
When you get home, you're too tired to do anything
but flop into bed and sleep in your makeup,
'cause that's a good idea. On your rare days off,
you spend all your time being lazy and farting around
on the internet. Why bother cooking for reals?
Now what do you think?
I think white rice with toppings is okay.
On to another topic!
When you're cooking, there are five
seasonings that are fundamental.
Ringo, would you care to list them off
with that perfect little poker face of yours?
Sugar is one of them. Salt is, too. Vinegar also.
And then...
And then?!
Huh? Uh...
Ur-urrr!
Sugar, salt, vinegar, der-der-der!
Der-der-der! Bwalala!
Enough smack-talk!
The other two are soy sauce and miso, now aren't they?
Miso horny!
Hey wait, isn't it a turn-on for guys
when they see a girl cooking for them?
No way! That's just...
You're home! Take me!
Ms. Becky, it's high time we
got down to making it, yeah?
What, a baby?
No, the food!
Okay, then! I'll get the cutting board!
Sorry about that, Ringo! My mistake!
Your chest is so flat,
I guess I thought it was the cutting-board!
Goodness, I am such a bonehead!
Maybe she'll have some boobs when she's older!
And for dessert, we'll make delicious strawberries
topped with condensed milk!
Wash and drain the berries, then put them in a bowl.
Then pour on the condensed milk and you're golden!
This stuff doesn't even count as cooking anymore.
Oh! And there I go again!
I meant to reach for the condensed milk,
and I went for the condensed boobies!
I mean, just look at them!
Go to your happy place!
The only reason I seem flat is because of Chubs
and the Boob Monster over there!
Don't call me "Chubs!"
What the hell?! "Boob Monster?!"
What's the matter, Ms. Becky?
You're really letting Ringo have it this afternoon.
'Cause I'm jealous, dammit!
Lay off the milk, okay?
Listen up, new girl!
Don't go getting full of yourself
just 'cause you're young!
Before you got here, the boys were all in love with me!
What world are you living in?
Kiss me, gorgeous!
I don't wanna!
So be it.
I'll just cook up your little crush, then!
You're on the menu, missy!
Today's special is Ringo breast, if I can find any meat!
Take your best shot, Grandma.
I don't think this is helpful!
Stand down, ladies!
When you have a dispute in the realm of home ec,
you settle it with a cook-off showdown!
Chef One! Ms. Kinoshita!
Miso soup?
Soup is pretty simple.
I don't know if this is going to do it.
Well, nobody said it had to be flashy.
It's just tofu, right?
We all like red miso a lot, so I'm glad she used it!
Good call there, Ringo!
Now, for the moment of truth!
What am I tasting?!
There's a strong fishiness to it, like a seafood stock,
and a smell that's making my eyes water!
The flavor is so rich, and so powerful!
It's almost too much, but there's something about it
that I just can't get out of my mind!
This bowl is a chalice given to us by the gods of miso,
and the blessed broth within
is a miracle to be cherished!
Is he nuts? I can't take another sip of this stuff.
It's sour, and kind of fishy.
It makes me feel all barfy.
Ringo!
What perfect food did you use to make this soup?
Old slippers.
You know that brown part of the insole?
Yeah, I mostly used that.
You cured my foot kink!
It made the soup stock really brown.
So the red miso you tossed in just for color?
Hey, you guys.
Can we name Becky the winner so I can go and throw up?
Yeah, no kidding. Whatever she made,
it's got to be better than this
foot-soup Ringo hit us with.
Not a chance. We have to try both for it to be fair.
Ms. Becky, it's your turn.
You're gonna like my dish.
I have every confidence you'll be coming back for more!
Huh? Just rice?
So, uh, what about a side dish?
That is the side! Here's the main course!
That's disgusting! Kill it with fire!
Well. Hurry up and eat.
Or else the best-by date will pass you by
That best by date's long gone!
You are a teacher, you nymphomaniac!
How have they not fired you yet?
Daddy's a big-shot politician. I'm not going anywhere!
Now all the mysteries are solved!
Come on, class! No need to be shy!
Here. Eat Ms. Becky!
Just do it!
That's a good class. Don't worry.
There is plenty of Becky to go around!
Huh? Uh, hold up.
This is not what I had in mind, fellas!
Heave-ho!
Not the going down I wanted... !
"If you make something good to eat...
...you'll have them lined up down the street."
'Til next time. "Let's Go Home Ec!"
So, there you have it.
Just another ordinary, average day like any other.
Kind of dull, actually. Well, there was that thing
that happened on the way back
from our shopping trip, I guess.
Is this it?
Mm-hmm.
Minotamo Rock Festival, huh?
If we get up to the stage and it looks like fun,
you guys maybe want to go up there and give it a shot?
We've never played in a band
together before... I don't know.
Well, I think the five of us could
fake our way through something.
She's right. If you're really
worried about how we'd sound,
then we could always go with
the visual kei route, you know.
We can even disguise Kinoshita,
if we go heavy on the make-up.
Visual kei, huh?
Yeah, sounds like fun!
We are gonna look so cool!
I'm going to irrigate your soul!
That could be a song!
Nope.
That stage is pretty small.
Just the right size for a bunch of noobs like us!
That's the spirit! Let's do it!
All right, folks, our next act is called AKB40!
I thought it was 48.
Isn't that?
Hey, guys! I missed you so much!
Ms. Becky?!
Now I get it! That wasn't a mistake!
AKB40 means... !
Ancient! Teacher! Becky! Age 40!
Here comes my latest song! "Give me a Man... Now!"
You and I now share the same last name,
No mistaking it's a different game.
"Catch ya' later's" just so hard to own;
Think I'd much prefer you said, "Honey, I'm home."
I'll wait patiently for you to shamble through the door.
Did I just hear a key in the lock?
Can I finally take my eyes off the clock?
Someone marry me!
I'm a catch, you'll see!
I'm so sick of chasing men from sea to shining sea!
Bachelor's hear my plea:
Take a chance with me!
Sweep me off my feet and let this ponytail fly free!
Thanks, you guys!
You're such a swell audience!
What was that...?
That just happened, right?
Receptions.
She's dealt with two decades of wedding karaoke.
Howled her needs into a mic time after time.
Think about it.
Is it so odd that she'd have a
couple of songs up her sleeve?
Not at all.
This next one is called: "Old People Smell Funny!"
One, two, thr... !
School Swim Trunks.