Time for the next phase of your farm education.
Your time in the rice paddy was instructive,
but I think you're ready for more.
Lesson number two is... going in dry!
There are tons of crops that grow in those conditions.
What're we gonna start her on?
Hmph.
The soybean.
Outta sight!
I chose them, not only because as novice farmers go,
they're a pretty forgiving crop,
but because the end-product
is such a Jack of all trades.
Miso, soy sauce, tofu, natto, cooked beans,
soymilk and soy flour.
They can also be made into bean sprouts or edamame.
Edamame is soybean, then?
You betcha!
The humble soybean.
So packed with nutrients and carbohydrates.
some call it "the meat of the field".
People eat it all the time, it's fairly common,
but that's just one use for this awesome legume.
In a bean-ocracy, they would be king!
When will it sprout up?
Soybeans grow pretty quickly.
Tonight, then?
Wow. You are so from the city.
Ten days' to two weeks' time, give or take.
All right!
Show them who's boss, Ringo!
As Ringo pushed those handy
little soybeans into the soil,
we had no idea that one of their products, miso,
would soon be leading me down the shirtless path
of yogurty hell!
Aww! Guys, we're out of miso!
Who feels like going on a supply run?
But doesn't that mean going up to Biotech?
Yeah.
What's a Biotech?
Oh. It's another class, like us.
Its full name's the Biotechnology Department.
We also call them Class B, which works out pretty well.
Miso is important, but...
Biotech...
I'm not a big fan of their class rep, to be honest.
Why's that?
He's totally weird.
He's so standoff-ish most of the time.
And then he's staring at you all funny-like.
Does he want to talk?
You look at him to engage him in conversation
but he runs away for safety.
Then stares some more.
Awkward...
Mm-hmm!
Fine then, don't talk to him. But if nobody mans
up, there won't be any miso soup at dinner.
I want soup, but...
Kousaku. We can do this.
Yeah. Okay.
You ready?
Yeah.
Miso!
Hell yeah!
Little did we know...
Up here, right?
So they say.
You don't know, then?
Ringo?! What the heck?!
I just wanted to know where the room was.
Oh, right.
I forgot you've never been up to Class B before.
We're kind of in the same the boat...
We've never actually gone inside.
Look at this stuff. What do they do with it?
Production's curriculum is very different than ours.
So they use all these machines?
It's like a lab in here!
Such is the power of science!
You...
You're Akari Suzuki, a.k.a. Bio Suzuki!
In the flesh. Minori said you
might be paying me a visit.
Here at Tamo No-Rin, the weirdest and strongest of us
are known as Farming's Top Four!
I never expected one of those
numbered students to be here!
Now, now.
Protocol dictates that I receive the Class A rep,
his bosom friend, and the rather much-discussed
transfer student with open arms.
If you want some miso, take your fill, Class A!
Smells yummy.
As well it should.
Only soybeans that had gone through a thorough
vetting process made it in.
Is that so?
Put some onto a cucumber.
It makes for a wonderful snack this time of year!
Hurry it up.
Will do.
I guess you're hungry, huh?
Thanks for this beany boon.
Not just yet.
Before you go, would you be kind enough to help me
with a trifling matter?
"Trifling matter?"
What's up?
I require... some test subjects!
I don't want to!
Easy, boys...
We developed a new product in Class B.
I merely need some help with a trial run.
Really?
What exactly did you make?
A Lactobacillus!
Lactobacillus?
Y'mean like that junk in yogurt?
Very good.
It makes lactic acid, and this latest batch,
complements of the Biotech Department,
is of the vegetable variety.
Yeah, as if!
Yogurt is made of milk.
I didn't just fall off of the turnip truck!
My poor boy, you must have metal in your head.
Lactobacilli are in rice bran pickles.
That miso you're holding.
You even find them floating in the air we breathe.
We call ours... !
Dun dun dun!
Anal BB! You like that?!
For "All Natural Life Science, Bio Type B".
It's the perfect acronym!
Ho-boy.
With a name like that,
I thought it was some kind of ointment
Apply directly to the anus.
Geez! Did you really have to blurt it out?!
I'm going to regret asking,
but exactly what sort of trial run did you have in mind?
Just testing the product in real-world conditions.
Specifically, this yogurt made from Anal BB.
A taste-test, huh?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
While I applaud your willingness to lend me a hand.
This isn't the kind of yogurt you eat.
Huh?!
No. It's the kind...
...you apply topically!
It's topical yogurt?
It's not for eating?
It's a fact.
Lactobacillus on crops reduces vermin attacks.
Not to mention the added
promotion of healthy germination.
This is common knowledge!
Even if the proof is anecdotal!
With that in mind, I thought Anal BB might help
other things grow, too!
Well, she did hook us up with the miso.
We're in her debt.
So what do you think? Want to give it a shot?
I'm game.
Bad call, self.
So, uh, where are our shirts?
What, and get Anal BB all over them?
I think not!
It's time for yogurt bukkake!
No need to get involved, Kinoshita.
Your face is plenty smooth without them
shooting all over it.
You down for Anal BB?
Yeah. Whatever you're packing, give me.
Ugh!
Fill me in. What's up with the camera?
Yeah, what's that about?
You troglodyte!
The answer to your question is patently obvious!
I owe it to science to document my results!
Now, less talkin' and more bukkak-in'!
Dude. Really?
Ah... !
Candid shots!
Skeet!
Skeet, skeet, skeet, skeet, skeet, skeet, skeet, skeet!
You fool! Why'd you aim for the chest?
Hit him in the glasses next time!
If you know what's good for you,
you'll shoot your wad on his lenses!
Fix his make-up!
Skeet!
Kei, this is a food experiment, isn't it?
Please tell me we're not in a yogurt porn.
Perhaps it's a little bit of both.
I'm ready for my close-up, Miss Suzuki!
Quiet on the set, men!
You, you, Splotch-a-Bro, scene two, action!
Aw, come on!
Don't sacrifice my dignity for
a film with a ripped-off title!
She swiped Hakusho!
Now I will show you my power at 80 percent!
Dude, not the time to quote it!
Uwegh!
What the hell? You're shipping us!
His bro-gurt is your destiny!
Hmm... That line. Put it in the fan-fic.
You idiot!
I don't want to be a Mary-Sue in my own slash!
What does all that even mean?!
Huh?!
Kei! Where're your pants?
Bro-gurt... Bro-gurt...
You-You don't want to do this!
No, please!
Glad you got it off!
These dailies are solid.
As a sign of thanks, I'll give you a "tip."
Say "hint", not "tip".
Even now as we speak, F is on the move.
So watch yourself.
Dear God! F?!
Go-go-go-go-go, got to go, got to go fast!
Kousaku!
What're you doing out here?
No! Go back! It isn't safe out here!
But waiting got boring.
So you threw your lives away
because you got a little antsy?!
What's got you all freaked out?
Legend tells of a class of great brutality.
Brute strength is the only law they choose to recognize!
Sowing terror among their foes for a century now,
these dervishes of doom formed
the backbone of our very school!
Their class is the letter...
F!
F, huh?
Yes! And the F stands for... !
fooling with the Woodmen is a fatal flaw,
friend-o!
Hey... I know you!
You're one of Farming's Top Four,
Class F rep Rintarou "Woodman" Miyoumoto!
Shut up, sapling!
I'm going to take you up to the House of Pain.
The Treehouse of Pain, that is.
How come, huh? What'd I do wrong?
Sure, play dumb.
You and I both know.
You talk to women so easy just to spite us!
The F in Class F is for "forest".
Of all the various departments,
Forest Engineering has the single harshest curriculum.
None of us graduate without first
surviving rigorous mortal combat.
We live up here six months outta twelve.
We're men! With wood in our hearts!
An' we're going to show you our wood!
This guy has no idea what he just said, does he?
Guys like you don't do anything
but mess around in the dirt
with seeds and junk, and you have two actual,
real-live girls following you around?!
That's balls!
Didn't a girl join your class this year?
She left the next day!
You Class A twerps bogart the knockout transfer student,
and that's bad enough, but watching you treat Nakazawa
like chopped liver hits us like a handsaw in the heart!
That's old-growth devotion, man!
Wait. Do you like her?
She's nice!
Cheerful!
Boobies!
Childhood friend!
Good cook!
She's got everything we Woodmen look for in a woman!
So why are you sprung for the new girl?!
Huh?
Yeah! I think the tree-dude's
making some good points there!
Listen up, Kousaku. And listen good.
Cause I'm only going to say this once.
Is it true that you and Nakazawa
here used to take baths together
'til you were in the ninth grade?
Huh?!
No, of course not! That's crazy-talk, man!
Yeah, I should've known better!
No guy is that kind of lucky!
It was only up until the eighth grade!
You son-of-a-bitch!
Wait! It's not what you're thinking, okay?
I haven't had a mom for years and years now,
and my dad works away from home in the winter.
Get to the bath part!
Dad sent me to live at Minori's house for a while.
There were too many kids to bathe alone
so my baths were with all four sisters.
You're telling me... You had four girls in the bath?!
At once?
Yup.
All right. You're dead!
I don't want to die just 'cause I kept up
with my personal hygene!
You didn't miss out on anything, trust me!
There were no branches on this
trunk, if you catch my drift!
No branches, huh?! What the hell's wrong with you?
Well it was the truth, wasn't it?!
Maybe then!
But maybe you should check out
these redwoods I'm packing now!
If you want to keep the tree simile afloat
they're more like bonsais.
Ah! Why're you being such a bastard?!
You know what?!
My bonsais and I are dragging you into the bath
for a rematch later today! If I'm really such a zero,
it shouldn't be a problem for you, right?!
Yeah, fine. I guess.
Not that I care either way...
That a boy!
I'm going to give your back a good scrubbing
the way I always used to!
Nah, I'm good!
No you're not!
There're some places we just can't get to.
You could wash my back, too.
It's only fair, you big butthead.
After that, we could take a
crack at each other's fronts!
Cute!
Huh. Eighth grade.
That story, is it true?
You were just joking, right?
Riny!
He looks tore up. What the heck?
It's because love-triangles are like poison to him!
Want to know something, Kousaku?
Yeah. I guess.
I.... I never got to sit next to a girl in class
not having girls or desks out here.
And I never will.
Not unless I take the bull by the horns, right?
Problems are like trees.
Unless I start chopping away at
them, they won't go down.
That's it, then. My mind's made up.
I'm going to give the Forest Engineering Department
such a spit-shine,
the ladies will be signing up in droves.
Yeah? How you figure?
We'll court them.
Court who?
Forest Girls!
The F in Class F is for Forest!
Yes, I speak of that fashion trend
that's taking the ladies by storm!
We'll be their lumberjacks of love!
What? That idea came and went, you guys.
She's right. They've moved on.
You'll need a time machine.
Shut up!
Can't you see how badly we need women up in here?!
If only we could sit next to one
and then forget our textbook,
so we'd have to share?
Or both of us go to pick up a dropped pencil at once
and our fingers touch?
And the group projects! Think of the group projects!
The F in Class F is for Female!
It's like they were raised on dating sims.
You know, they might actually find the right ones yet.
While it's true that the Forest Girl fad
didn't have quite so much in the way of staying power,
there's a new breed of athletic, outdoorsy women
who might just be what you guys are looking for.
You mean it? Take a knee, fellas!
I'm talking about. Mountain Girls!
Mountain Girls!
They go hiking on rock-strewn trails.
And some of them even mountain-climb.
This growing trend could bring
them right to your doorstep!
The F in Class F is for Mt. Fuji!
Back to the summit! To await our womens!
I hope they're cool with a hell of a wait.
It seems Rintarou has lost.
Of Farming's Top Four, he is the weakest.
He's a disgrace to our good name,
defeated by a mere lack of women.
It's time for a snack, my tender morsel.
Huh? Maybe she's just running late or something.
Hmm... She said she'd be here, though.
Wonder what's up?
Well, if she's not out here,
I don't know where to look.
No! Her book!
You're seventeen? Serendipitous.
As years go, that one is molto bellissimo.
Aren't you the same age?
I am seventeen at every age.
Numbers of its ilk are known as prime.
They're lonely in their indivisibility.
A loneliness I know only too well.
That's enough!
I knew that it was you, Class E rep, Rose Hanazono!
Why, yes, I am!
I've got your number!
You're a student in the Landscaping Department,
and you're one of Farming's Top Four,
not to mention the fact you're
the hottest guy in school!
None of that gives you the right to kidnap Ringo!
For that, your life is forfeit!
Hey, Kousaku.
Please tell me your virtue is still intact!
Why'd you no-show at the library, huh?
He offered me snacks, so...
How the heck have you even survived this long?!
And you! Did I or did I not tell you to never ever
mess around with Class A girls again?!
Oh yeah? So what did he do before?
He tried putting the moves on Minori about a year ago.
You still recall that?
Her too, I'll wager.
Know what happens when a hot guy
hits on a girl like Minori?!
She loses her damn mind, that's what!
You're all she wanted to talk
about for the next three weeks!
I get what I want, my dear boy, no matter the cost.
It's a good policy to have...
Eh?
You don't get to add her to the list 'cause she's...
not for sale!
That's just lip-service.
Like hell!
The Pockin knows your measure.
Face me in crunchy combat!
Where did you... get that?
The rules are few.
We start chewing at it from either side.
Whoever breaks it apart or flinches first is the loser.
Have at you, churl!
Trial by Pockin! With Ringo as prize to the victor!
Bring it on!
Don't fret, Ringo! I've got this one in the bag!
He's really going on the offensive, huh?!
What?!
Hanazono closed his eyes! He's not backing off at all!
He just keeps nibbling!
My heart is pounding!
The heat from his face is burning me up!
Stop this game! It's a trap!
And not a single moment to spare.
Kousaku, I need you to step away
from that man on the double!
Rose Hanazono is class rep of
the Landscaping Department,
but the landscape that interests
him most is right in front of him!
I was too late!
Get your mouth off of him!
That right there is the money shot!
I have tasted the rainbow!
Your first kiss wasn't Ringo! It was me, 'Zono!
You have a lot of nerve, don't you!
Indeed.
How long I've waited for this moment.
It was di molto bellissima!
Then... you couldn't care less about Minori or Ringo!
Go on!
You used them to get to me 'cause you're... !
Yes! I am!
Well I am not, so slow your roll, hot-lips!
And you guys just sat back and let this happen?
You betcha!
Your uke hi-jinks will play out
fantastically in my doujinshi!
How come I got to be the uke?!
There's a big gay world waiting for you!
I'm fine right here!
It's all because he bathed with me!
Your boobs are great, okay?!
Hey.
You need something, Ringo?
One, Bio Suzuki.
Two, Woodman Rintarou.
Three, Rose Hanazono.
Mm... So?
Aren't there four?
Next time on No-Rin,
the last member of Farming's Top Four will arrive!
Probably could've done all this
in one episode, but whatever!
Full-Moe Alchemist: Bounty.