I am so tired.
Changing outta these clothes and grabbing
some dinner sounds awesome right about now.
Where are my Yukatan posters?!
My Yukatan wall scrolls?! My Yukatan body pillow?!
My Yukata DVD and BluRay collection?!
My scrapbook of Yukatan-related news articles?!
Yeah, Dumped them in the furnace.
Don't say I never do nothing for you.
What would possess you to burn my posters?!
Hey! Would you feel comfortable in a room
with pictures of you all over the damn wall?!
I did you a favor so your dream girl won't freak out.
She doesn't need to know how obsessed you are.
And besides, your mom begged me to do something.
I promised her I'd watch your back out here,
so get used to it.
Well. You could've asked.
Don't read too much into it 'cause just so you know
I'm going to do everything in my power to make sure
you never hook up with that little slut.
Believe me, I know why she's here.
And if Little Miss Pop Sensation
thinks this is the place
to stink up her would-be green thumb,
she's got another thing coming!
That doesn't even make sense.
Oh, doesn't it?!
Whatever, who cares?!
Her first time working the farm is
supposed to be tomorrow morning, correct?
I think so.
Well, Her Highness is due for a trial by fire!
Hmph!
Alrighty then.
Does that mean what I think it does?!
'Cause if the girl I've known
since we were playing doctor
has it in for the girl who made my gonads drop...
Not that I'm proud of this, but the whole thing might be
a little too hot for me to handle.
Huh. I give her credit for even bothering to show up.
Yeah?
Well if she knew you were planning to put her
through her paces, she probably wouldn't have.
Of all the days for Kei to be out on a
welding gig for shop class. This is balls.
I will own this whore!
Why do I always end up having to
deal with this crap by myself?
That didn't take long.
Don't be shy.
C'mon down and show us all how you look in the uniform.
Sure thing.
What the hell is wrong with you?!
She looks like... She looks like a tentacle magnet!
Huh.
Must've given her the wrong outfit.
In what way exactly does that suit
of comic-shop stripper-pole armor look anything
like one of our work uniforms?!
I know what you're up to and it's just wrong!
Ugh. What I'm up to is for her own good. Hmph.
She can't work in that!
She'd better learn how quick,
'cause the first test she's
got is coping with distraction!
If she wants to work the earth,
she's got to get over caring how she looks!
All the more reason not to stuff her
into something out of an online fan fic!
This whole thing is ridiculous,
I'm putting my foot down!
I'm okay.
See? She's down with this.
Now then.
Just to show you I'm a good sport...
Yup. Say hi-di-ho to girl power!
Hyah!
Hey!
Wha... ?!
Whoa-whoa!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
I... can't... take it!
Whoa. This is so hot!
Yeah, no. Rein it in there a bit, tiger.
Huh? Wait. No! That just came out!
Hmph.
Heh! You know, Miss Kinoshita,
if you're self-conscious you can back out now.
Like hell.
Of course.
Holy crap, it's a Paladin!
Or just Kei. Seriously, dude? A suit of armor?
I thought you were supposed to be out welding.
I felt a disturbance in the force.
And I like to watch.
Welcome to the Cucumber House.
Hey, Yukatan. Can I get an autograph?
Screw her, man, look at this one!
Now that's some produce!
The First job's a cinch.
All you have to do is check the leaves for diseases
and what not. See any bugs having a party,
you pick 'em off. Understood?
I'll play nice and give you the row on the left.
One on the right's mine.
Battle starts when Kousaku says go.
If he can do it without drooling.
Wait, why me?
Go on. It's the easiest job in the world, I promise.
Okay fine, whatever. Just do it.
And they're off! In full cosplay!
Minori's a sneaky one when she wants to be.
Huh?
Don't get me wrong,
cucumber's a beginner plant, sure. We all know that,
it's just...
If you're not ready for the prickly bits on the leaves
and stems, that stuff can sting like a mother.
Are you saying Minori put her in bikini armor
on purpose to get her pricked?!
Minori knows her cucumber; she's used to it.
City gal like Ringo, though.
I'd say she's in for a rude awakening.
Wow. Look at her go! She's a demon!
Game over, man.
Wait. No. Not yet.
Not until Minori wipes the floor with her.
Ahh... Oh, right. I totally forgot.
Yuka may be naturally immune to the prickly bits.
But what about the caterpillars?
Bingo.
Those things make even
a seasoned cumcumber-er's skin crawl.
And now we see what she's made of.
No! She's too wet behind the ears for this!
Get an eyeful of those cute little
buggy-wuggies and bawl yourself sick.
"Um. Bye, everybody: I'm going back to the Big City
where the only insects I have to worry about are flies!"
Whooa!
Oh snap. Keinez the Catalyst goes Oratorio!
That's what you call the power of bikini armor, guys!
Of course! Ringo's never seen a caterpillar before!
How would she know to be grossed out by one?!
She's too innocent and pure
to realize how vile they are!
Oh my glob, this is amazing!
Whoa! She's closing the distance
between them like nobody's business!
Nice try, sister,
but I didn'tt sign on to be
the laughing stock of my peers!
Clear! Clear!
Clear-clear-clear-clear-clear-
clear-clear-clear-clear...!
Clear!
Photo finish!
Nuh-uh, dude: Nakazawa won by a nose!
Bag, please.
Heh! Yeah, well don't rest on your laurels just yet.
This battle is far from over.
Next up, we have the Hen House!
Alongside rice farming, cleaning the chicken coops
is the most important part of a
freshman Ag student's training.
If you can handle what's on the other side of that door,
you can handle anything.
Good luck in there!
Hens are a barnyard predator's dream.
If we didn't keep them penned up,
we'd have nothing but bones and feathers come morning.
The coops are great, but the downside
is they're humid and, well, cooped.
First one of us to make the floor shine
without losing her lunch takes home the gold!
Feathers got to go. Food scraps got to go.
Poop's got to go.
And if feathers, food scraps,
and poop are too much for you,
you've got to go.
Whoa! It's nothing to her.
She's acclimated to the smell!
Don't call it yet!
We're still just getting started!
That's right.
The putrid aroma is only the
beginning of her season in hell!
The smell you deal with. The heat you deal with.
But then...
Abandon all hope ye who enter here!
Oh. Hey, hon? I love the energy,
but I think you might've overlooked something important.
Can't forget about the feed stall, can we?
Aah!
Whoa!
Aaagh!
It's like a cockroach Armageddon
every time we open that door!
Just think about it, man:
Darkness, humidity, an all-you-can eat poop buffet.
This is paradise for them!
That's right!
Dealing with cockroaches is part of the job!
Admit defeat and I'll help you clean them out.
Ewww! She's stepping on them!
I'm going to say what we're all thinking
and call this beyond gross.
Disqualification! Y-You're supposed to be freaking out!
Sorry.
So, is that it?
And the winner is, Ringo Kinoshita!
Huh?!
Nice.
No! Not yet! She isn't done!
Minori, please. Give it up.
We still have to test her most basic agricultural skill!
Trial by Rice Field!
Rice field?
Oh, yes!
Rice has been a vital part of the Rising Sun experience
since the Yayoi Period!
You can't claim to know what it is to be Japanese
until you've gotten your feet wet! I defy you to try!
Only after you've mastered our landscaping and
dietary epicenter will I allow
you to count yourself worthy!
Uh. Don't oversell it.
Or, stop talking outta your ass.
Argue all you want. History is on my side!
But don't worry.
Back out now and I'll spare you the embarrassment!
Bring it.
Someone's feeling feisty, huh?
All-righty, then.
So, meet at the rice fields Saturday morning
dressed in clothes you don't mind getting water-logged.
Woo-hoo.
This field's roughly one tenth of a hectare.
That's about a thousand square meters.
It takes four people half a day to plant rice.
Hah! Prepare to watch me set a new world record, losers!
Um. Before we get started I'd like to clarify something.
Usually when you're about to take the plunge.
It's a good idea to dress in
clothes appropriate to the task.
But, uh... Seriously, you guys, this is just...
I mean, c'mon.
Sorry. Should I change?
Nah, it's okay. No worries.
You definitely rack up points for thinking ahead.
And looking fly!
You, however!
What's wrong?
What do you mean "What's
wrong?" Have you seen yourself?!
I mean, okay, yes, technically it is a bathing suit,
so it qualifies as appropriate
for getting wet in and all.
But, other than that,
nothing about what you have on isn't wrong!
I can't un-see this, man! Not cool!
Well you'd be the first to want to un-see it.
Don't even! That's just...
Where do you go that people encourage this?!
Let's just say somewhere popular.
And sopping wet.
Mah! Never mind, dude!
Everybody loves to see the Gaisenmon.
Whoa, highbrow!
That's like a French English play on words, bro.
It's a combo of English for dude
and French for Arc of Triumph!
That's why Kei's a trailblazer
and we're just a couple of followers!
I'm just happy we get to bask in his presence!
Look, Kei.
I'm not trying to tell you what to wear, but...
I mean we got to consider the ladies, right?
Poor Ringo doesn't need to...
Give me a second, I'm in the middle of something.
Kei is a living god!
Wait, don't encourage him!
Hey! I see you there!
That's the point, silly!
Has the world gone mad?
This is an Ag school, you're a teacher here!
Why would you wear something like that to farm in?
Oh, sweetie.
Wedding dresses are meant to get soiled.
I'ma need you to not elaborate on that, please!
Uh-oh. Have I crossed a line? I'm such a naughty girl.
Somebody really needs to teach the teacher a lesson.
Okay, you're like a hundred
years old and that's super bleh.
But the experts say I'm at my peak.
Stop hitting on your students and go home!
We don't need you to supervise!
Oh stop playing hard to get:
this is every teenage boy's fantasy.
I just want to plant rice!
Why is that so difficult to let me do?!
I don't need this! I don't deserve this!
You'll never sow your seed in
a field wetter than this MILF,
lover boy!!
How has the school board not
axed you twice-over by now?!
Whooaa...
You're only a MILF if you actually have children!
Thank you. That was, uh, that was getting kind of weird.
Hmm. Meh. Minori's got your back.
Hey, Minori? What're those?
What? Bloomers.
Wait...
Did you...?
Behold.
A deeper shade of blue than
sky on a Spring Afternoon. Wow.
Okay, I'm not trying to say they're hideous or anything.
But what's the story with these things?
You've read the student handbook, right?
Girls are supposed to wear shorts.
It's no big deal.
I had them sent to me special for today.
No joke?!
Whoa! Historic!
I can't remember the last time I saw a pair like these.
Didn't know they were still a thing.
They're not new or anything.
Just a hand-me-down from my sisters.
Damn it, Minori, what is wrong with you?!
What?
I was adjusting the hem to cover up a mosquito bite.
Well, it's mighty suggestive!
When you're dressed like that,
there's just some things you can't do!
Hems have been playing fast and loose
with men's short-term memory since the caveman days!
The bloomers are too much! Disqualification!
Control yourself for five minutes
and they wouldn't be an issue.
Creep.
Whoa, whoa! Don't turn this into a feminist rant.
You chose them!
Deal with it, pervert!
Wait. What the...  What do you think you're doing?!
Yeah! Show us some of that sweet swimsuit action!
School swim team uniform.
Bold choice. Very "kyu-suku."
Kyu-suku?
Now listen closely.
Kyu-suku refers to a popular old style swimsuit.
The distinguishing feature of
its design is the crotch area
being divided into two discreet regions.
This ingenious shape allowed the wearer
greater flexibility both in and outside of the pool.
it also protected the susceptible
female nether regions from getting water-logged.
Form and function combined to
make a truly wonderful thing.
Yep, this beaut was a game-changer.
Wow. You guys know water sports.
Well, either way I'm a fan of the style.
It's just the right balance of functional and girlie.
And I know nothing about fashion.
I'm just shooting from the hip.
Don't look at me like that.
My bad! I, uh...
I just think you look great in that.
I mean it totally suits your curves.
Kind of makes you look like a model.
You... pervert.
Forgive me! I won't look anymore promise!
Chauvinist!
Please. Ladies, you got to stop this.
The landscape students are gawking.
Is it too much to ask that we all just get along?
Stay out of it!
Okay, look, I'm only trying to point out
that we're about to start the whole rice-planting thing,
so it's probably best if everyone lets bygones
be bygones.
Ready when you are.
Alrighty, folks!
Let's get this show on the road and start cultivating!
Pay no attention to that.
Only a little mud between the toes.
You'll get used to it.
You might even find it kind of pleasant.
Oh, okay.
First up: Let me show you how to plant properly.
You're really good at this.
Huh? You... You think so?
Around here, Kousaku's the man when it comes to rice.
His technique is legendary.
True fact: in class,
the teachers don't hold a candle to him.
Yeah. Back home, they all used to call me
"the rice cultivating mad man."
No worries. It's not as hard as it looks.
I call foul!
In case you haven't noticed,
we're trying to run a race here.
This is hardly the time for one-on-one instruction!
Not so fast! Girl's got a right to be taught.
I say let him. We want a fair competition.
He can give her everything she
needs to know in a few minutes.
Fine then, teach her your "legendary technique." But!
You'd better not be stalling for time!
Yeah, yeah.
Let's see what you got. Can you do it like I showed you?
Yes.
Not too shabby, but you got to stick
it down in the mud a tiny bit deeper.
See, the way you've got it in
there now it'll get washed away.
So...?
Deeper.
Watch me.
You see how far I'm putting it down in there? Bam.
We have to make sure the roots are supported well. Yeah?
It's kind of hard to see.
Sure. Kind of.
Ugh! Come on already! Let's go!
Miss Becky could get a date in half the time.
Just look at her!
Any longer and the poor woman is going to shrivel up!
Take it from me: life is cruel.
Idea. Why don't you two race as a team?
She leads, you come from behind.
Yeah, but for that to work,
our bodies will have to be touching...
Actually, what am I complaining about?
This is a solid plan. I'm excited to be a part of it.
Wait! I'm not liking this! What is it teaching her?
Minori, give it a rest.
At the end of the day, she's here to learn,
not worry about whether you
think she can pass the muster.
This is just too... ! Look at this thought bubble!
They're basically spooning,
how can I be comfortable with that?
Ringo. Are you okay with touching?
Sure.
Seriously?!
This won't come back to bite me in the ass?!
Nope.
Wait.
"Nope, not seriously" or "nope" as in "we're" cool?
Bah! I'm in either way!
'Kay, so...
Look out below, mud's slippery! Timber!
Oh, I'm such a klutz!
Not as sure on my feet as I thought I was.
Maybe I need some one-on-one tutoring.
Do you charge, or what?
Uh, in case you haven't noticed, Minori,
we're trying to run a race here.
Asshole.
All right. Since Miss Kinoshita is the beginner,
we'll start her from there.
Miss Nakazawa, being the expert,
will start slightly behind.
The big moment is almost upon us.
The tension in the air is thick.
Welcome to the No-Rin Rice Planting Cup.
Kousaku and myself will be your hosts.
Thank you, it's good to be here.
We're waiting for Miss Becky to do the honors.
Ready.
Go!!
Man, look at her go!
Nakazawa has started strong.
But will that breakneck pace
take her to the finish line?
Bear in mind, Kei,
the girl has a reputation for stamina.
And it's clear she intends to use it
to bring the heat down on her opponent.
One has to question what Kinoshita's plans are
once the two are neck and neck.
Come on!
Conserve your energy or you're
going to burn yourself out!
Yeah-yeah! Go, Ringo!
Slow and steady wins the race!
What the challenger lacks in speed
she makes up for in attention to detail.
You know, at the end of the day, with a view like this
it doesn't even matter who brings it home.
How does that work?
Give it a ponder, man!
For centuries men have been in one of two camps:
You dig that ass, you're a perv.
Ta-tas and you're a mama's boy.
Brothers have been killing
each other over the difference
since forever!
He's right!
This competition is like a peace treaty!
Whoa-ho!
Bloomers!
Swimsuit!
Bootay!
Ta-tas!
There's something for everyone!
No longer must a man choose!
Nakazawa is swiftly closing the gap!
It's only a matter of moments before she takes the lead!
Stop glaring. Just give up.
No way.
Look, deny all you want but I'm telling you:
It's time you make peace with the fact
you're not cut out for this lifestyle.
Whatever you say.
Alright. That's it. You're through!
Oops. Sorry.
Ha! Hey, no worries. Accidents happen.
Occupational hazard when you're a stupid slut!
Jackass.
Oh, that's it! I'm done playing nice with you!
You stupid little hussy! You're going down!
Quit being such a bitch.
I'll show you bitch, bitch!
And it looks like they've gone from rice planting
to mud wrestling! We've got a spank fight!
I'd say so. I don't know about
you, Kei, but I'm riveted.
We should probably stop them.
You've had your fun, ladies!
Stop trampling the rice field!
Damn but this is hot!
Get away from me!
This was a bad idea!
That all you got, jail bait?
Bring it, Bloomers!
Oh, boy.
You know, you're actually pretty good.
Not as good as you.
It's funny sometimes, the things that'll make
two people want to bury the hatchet.
That's life for you, I guess.
Oh, don't worry. I re-planted the rice the next day.
Not with Miss Becky.
"The Smile You Showed Me."