Thing is, I want to be there for you.
Any village that raised you must be wonderful.
Thank you for coming ladies and germs!
How y'all doing this lovely country morn'?
Finer than frog hair!
Alrighty! Now the moment you've all been waiting for!
Let's get the first annual Aioi
village mixer up and running!
What do you say, folks?!
Who's ready to mingle and slam
headfirst into your soul mate?
Here you go, ma'am.
We got a live one.
I need you to get in there and run interference for me.
Huh? What's up?
Be discreet. There's a cougar at your
8 o'clock liable to chase off the men.
Let her sink her claws into you for a bit.
Eh? Okay, we must be talking about a real piece
of work if she makes you uncomfortable. Wow.
Deal is, no one's gonna buy the age she put down.
Granted we all fudge the numbers a tad
when we're looking to bag a mate, but this is absurd.
She's just... Well, see for yourself.
I mean... Damn...
Where is she?
Holy crap! You've gotta be kidding me! Miss Becky?
What are you even doing here?!
And why do you look like Ramses' the Great?!
Forget it, General, I can't!
You know this bag of bones?
She's my teacher.
Good, so there's no ice to break.
Go get her, chief! You're my hero!
Miss Becky, is that you?
Almost didn't recognize you, you look so...
eh, slender...
I'm on a new anti-aging regimen.
Strict fasting. That's the secret.
Revitalizes the cells.
Huh. That's nice. Wow. Fasting.
I bet is shaves years off... Not
that you have that many years
on your back to shave off in the first place, of course!
But you know what'll work even better?!
Goin' organic!
Mega refreshed!
Poo! And here I've been trying
so hard to stay disciplined!
You're a terrible influence!
Please stop looking at me like that.
Sorry, my love! Old habits die hard.
Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt. Is this seat taken?
No. Please. Be my guest.
Oh my, aren't we a perfect gentleman?
A-buh-bayummm!
So anyway, so they were all up in arms
about the skirt being too short.
See, I'm in a better place about my legs now.
Skinny jeans. That's the goal.
I've gotta do something!
Miss Becky's being swallowed by the generation gap!
Hey, there! Hungry?
Made fresh by the Aioi Wives Association!
Oh, how cute! That smell really takes me back.
Kind of reminds me of cafeteria food.
I know, right? Like whale fritters!
Fritters? Do what?
Just where did you go to school
that they served you whale?
My grandparents used to eat that kind of stuff.
Miss Becky, no!
It's too late.
I've held back as long as I could stand.
I must unleash!
Crap! Not that! Anything but that!
Forty-ish... Dimension!
Believe it or not, home skillets:
Life before the dot com bust
was all that and a bag of chips!
Uh... O-kay. Is it just me, or did it get seriously 90s
up in here?
What you want, what you really, really want!
Wow, that's neat.
Uh... I'm going to go get us all some refills.
No you don't, Skinny Jeans!
Well, that was... a thing.
Yeah. Yeah, it was.
So, what brings a lady like you
to a country mixer like this?
I mean, farming's so yesterday, right?
Oh, no! Farming's awesome! Really!
Hunky men, working with their hands...
Girls love that whole thing right now.
I guarantee you every woman here's in the market
for a farm boy.
But what's the appeal?!
It's not like there's any money working the soil.
Just back-breaking labor sunup to sundown.
Oh, come on. It's exotic.
At least it is when you're from the big city.
Really? But... I mean...
I'd think the big city would be more exotic
than a pile of dirt like this.
Right...? This is nowheres-ville.
Are you kidding?!
You have no idea what it's like in the city!
There's traffic congestion, office politics,
sexual harassment suits,
dog-eat-dog corporate takeovers...
A real farm beats a cube-farm any day!
At least here you're not just a cog in the machine!
Huh...
Sorry.
But you see my point, don't you?
Friends of yours?
I'm his queen.
And I'm his knocked-up wife.
How's it going, folks?
We good? Y'all enjoying yourselves or what?
How about a little game to loosen things up?
Maybe spice this party up a notch!
It's time to give our "First Impressions!"
Here's how it goes:
I'll unveil a word from the easel and ask,
"Who's the most-whatever the
word happens to be," okey-doke?
Then, you point to the person in your group
you think that applies to!
Ugh.
Oh! This'll be fun!
I'm liking this.
Alright, round one: go!
Let's see now...
Who's the cutest?
Yeah, you got it.
Come on, silly. Which of us you going to point to?
Yeah, yeah. You gotta pick one.
Uh... Well...
I think it's pretty obvious who I'm going to go...
Oh, that's so adorable. My honey-baby's... SHY!!
Yeouch!
Sounds like things are really
starting to heat up out there, huh?
Moving on up to round two.
Who at your table is the kindest?
Sweet pea, you must be exhausted.
Why don't you let me give you a massage?
Uh-oh. Somebody looks thirsty. Baby wanna drink?
Uh... Sure, why not? Thank you?
Hi-yaah!
Not the face!!
Here! Bottoms up, darling!
Tee-hee.
So... Who is it?
Forfeit!
Next up!
Who in your group is the chubbiest?
Oh now, now. Be nice.
Didn't your mother teach you not to lie?
Don't get defensive.
So you've packed on a few pounds since coming here.
There's no shame in that.
Ho-ho, things are really popping now!
Shoulders back! Who's the flattest?
Me! Me! You could roll dough on this chest!
Huh? Huh?!
Okay, folks! We're about to get real up in here!
Bring your A-game, it's the final round!
Who's...
Don't keep us in suspense!
Who's the person you most want to marry
and spend the rest of your life with?!
Kousaku!
Koutan!
Pick one!
Geez, nothing like putting me on the spot, huh?
I choose...
To run the hell away!
Hmph. Someone's got cold feet.
Nice try, slick.
Son of a...  Why do you have me all dolled up
in this monkey suit?!
Heh. You referring to the tux or the ropes?
Enough of this, huh?
Shouldn't I technically be in a hakama anyway?
We had you in one of those for the engagement ceremony.
For the wedding we want more
of an East meets West kind of thing.
Are you out of your mind?!
You want to kick off my married life
by pissing off the local gods?!
I'm begging you here, Kousaku.
Please.
Ugh. Can I at least ask you a question first?
Why'd you come back here? You hated this town.
You'd been chomping at the bit
to leave since I've known you.
World's too small.
Huh?
No matter how far you go, you always end up
back where you started, or someplace just like it.
Wherever you run to,
there's always something holding you down.
Always someone pissed at you.
She abandoned ship once.
Stands to reason she'll do it again.
Hell, you run long enough...
...pretty soon you find out
you're just running in place.
Deal is...
...sometimes the only way get where you're going
is to face where you're from.
Think about it.
You a runner?
I don't know.
Attention everyone. Attention please.
The Nakazawa-Hata wedding ceremony beings now.
Before we bid welcome to the bride and groom,
Allow me to introduce their friends Ringo Kinoshita
and Becky Natsumi, our stunning bridesmaids.
Ah, and the bride's darling little sisters,
Takumi and Akina, who are thrilled to be
our flower girls.
Erectile dysfunction, emotional unavailability.
Wandering eyes. Passive aggression.
Breakdown of communication. Backbiting in-laws.
Welcome to matrimony!
Now, if you'd join me, let's, uh...
Let's give a warm round of applause to our groom!
Next, the gorgeous, young bride-to-be.
Escorted by one very proud papa!
Oh, wow! She looks beautiful!
They met, I presume, like many of you here.
As children.
Kousaku moved to Aioi with his parents,
who came to our humble little village with big dreams
and a lot of heart.
Sadly, before the family could realize its ambitions
of living off the land,
Kousaku's beloved mother passed away.
Minori was a beacon and pillar of strength
for the bereft young boy.
She's right.
Minori was always there for me when things got rough.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you would...
We ask, with a prayer in our hearts,
that you give your blessing.
That you recognize and let be fulfilled the love
these two earnest souls have for each other;
a love that has triumphed over
grief and made them strong.
Please, Son, take care of my precious little girl.
Treat her like the best friend she is.
Hang on.
Does this mean we're not going
to be best friends anymore?
What?
I want to be your best friend.
You can't have more than one!
Oh, sweetie, don't worry.
Nothing's really gonna change.
He's still going to love you like he always has.
It's just that... Well, when two people marry,
they've gotta be best friends.
That's how it works, okay?
But we're still buddies with you.
No!
Taku?
I'm his best friend! You don't have to get married!
Uh... Yeah, we kinda do. I'm having his baby.
No you're not! You're just saying that!
Huh?
I know the difference between a baby and a kangaroo!
What on earth?
Surely it's too small to be a kangaroo?
Exactly what are you people trying to pull?!
Okay, everyone, please settle down!
We're trying to have a wedding here.
I don't think you're trying to have a wedding at all!
What is the meaning of this?!
What have you tricked us all into?!
This whole thing's a lie!
But that speech! It... It was so heartfelt!
Outrageous!
No, wait... We, uh...
I demand an explanation immediately!
Do these kids even know each other?!
Met when they were children my foot!
They... !
Wait.
Forgive me!
I'm sorry! If you're looking
for someone to blame, it's me.
From beginning to end,
this whole stupid fiasco has been my fault!
I never... It was never meant to go this far!
What started as a dumb joke went off the rails
and just spun completely out of control!
I... I was scared. My back was against the wall.
My only option was to see it through to the end.
Hooligan! So you string us along?!
Oh, well done! Bang up job representing your town!
I... I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. Truth is...
I hated this town!
I got dragged here. No one gave me a say.
I was a kid; my parents were intent on becoming farmers
and I was going to be a part of
it whether I liked it or not.
I watched as their dreams crumbled.
As "good, clean living" chewed 'em up and spat 'em out.
We weren't even a family anymore when it was all over.
I was left behind.
Only thing for me to do was take up farming.
It's hard work.
Especially when you don't wanna do it.
All I ever thought about was the
day when I could finally leave.
But through it all,
there was one person who gave me hope.
A pop singer.
Ah!
Her songs, her TV shows... all of it... was magical.
The big city life she always sang about
seemed so far away, so perfect.
I wanted to be a part of it.
Thinking about her got me through the worst of times.
She buoyed me up.
Yeah, that's right. I hated living in this town.
It's tiny, impoverished, in the middle of nowhere.
But then... she came here.
She saw, and for some crazy reason,
she loved everything about it.
She opened my eyes to the beauty of Aioi,
and suddenly, the things I spent half my life
waiting to get away from felt as magical as her voice.
"Give me this view and the clean air any day.
Any village that raised you must be wonderful."
That's what she said to me, and for the first time...
I understood.
Country life shaped me into who I am.
Look around you.
Warts and all, this little backwater town
inspired me to put myself on the line
to try and convince you to love it.
Look, You seem like nice people
and I'm not proud that I fooled you.
But the point I'm trying to make is:
I've learned there's actually a lot to love
about this little place.
That's all I wanted to say.
Kousaku?
Ringo.
Hey.
Minori?
So, I guess...
You really prefer Ringo over me after
all, now don't you?
She was the one who made life bearable, not me.
It's not like that. This isn't about choosing one.
It's about finding the middle ground.
You see?
We don't need to shun the city
for the country, or vice versa.
We just need to connect them.
The country feeds the city and
reminds people of their roots.
The city gives people something to aspire to.
A bird needs two wings to fly,
we need each other to survive.
Why feel we have to favor one over the other
when the whole point is to have both?
When you stop and think about it,
all of human history has been building to this!
See? We need one another!
You, Minori. And you, Ringo.
It's like I'm the bird.
And you two are my wings!
Saying a lot happened this
summer is an understatement.
But there's one important thing
all the craziness has taught me...
Yep.
If I've learned anything over the past few months,
it's that we all still have a lot to learn.
Mad cow! Mad cow!
Ageha!
Kousaku?
Hey.
Huh? What's up?
Go get him!
Not again! We've been through this already!
Some life, huh?
This has been Kousaku Hata,
and if you liked this, oh-ho!
Just you wait!