The Takaido Fushinari cucumbers
are coming along nicely.
The Wase Shinkuro eggplants
should be ready for harvest soon.
I give them a few more days.
Apart from the tomato splitting debacle.
It's been a very successful year.
Hello. Thank you for calling
Tamo-No-Rin, how can I help you?
Hello?
Kei?
It's you... How did you find me?!
You didn't really think you could escape, did you?
Come back right now.
I will not!
You and me, we're done, do I make myself clear?!
I'll be paying you a visit very soon.
If I were you, I'd get ready.
One phone call... and it all comes flooding back.
My past rears its ugly head yet again.
Oh no! Everyone, I have terrible news!
With an entrance that dramatic,
this better be important.
It's bad. I don't know how else to put it
other than to say the Principal broke.
Wait. He broke? Huh?!
Whoa. Is this the same mighty Principal I used to know?
The legendary warrior who killed
a bear with his own two hands?
What's that?
No, I'm afraid you won't be
able to speak to the bear today.
Okay.
It's clear he's completely lost his
mind, but why are we here?
Well, that's a great question. For the eggplants!
The eggplants?
Eggplants!
He keeps rambling on about
eggplants and I have no idea why.
Stop it!
It's not like we have a shortage of eggplants out there.
Why don't you just give him some already?
Yeah, that's the whole problem.
I've already given him eggplants,
but then he started saying,
"Hey. These are not real eggplants!"
Rrgh... Oooh, that burns me up!
Do you mind if I take a look at them?
Maybe there's something wrong?
Knock yourself out.
They seem perfectly edible, in my expert opinion.
Well, he disagrees.
And since these don't fit the bill,
I figured we could use our own eggplants instead,
which is why I brought you all here to save the day.
Ahhh...
I see. Yeah.
You're hoping for some sort of heartwarming
"after school special" plot, aren't you?
"The sad, forlorn principal snaps out of it
thanks to his devoted students."
Seen it before.
Geez, how unsentimental can you get?
The principal's instincts are right.
Huh?
Those eggplants. Not a single one of them is real.
They're manufactured.
Wait. What makes you say that?
Yes, what exactly are you blathering on about?
Sorry, but you're wrong, I've tried them myself.
They're thick, fresh, firm, and quite the mouthful.
See?
I can put the whole thing inside.
Listen to me.
If you let me use the home-ec room tomorrow.
I'll show you what a real eggplant looks like.
Oh, eggplant.
All right then, mister, you said you'd show us
the real deal, so bring it on!
I just hope your stuff has what it takes, Kei.
If it disappoints, then I'm stuck with
your itty-biddy eggplant either way, huh?
It's all yours.
Kei, no! Surely you don't mean that?
I appreciate your confidence, but let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
To begin, why don't we take a good, hard look
at the eggplants I've brought to the table?
Top of the line and one hundred percent organic.
Farm to table. Five hundred a piece!
That's a lot?
You gotta be kidding me! That's, like, crazy expensive!
It's your move, Kamatori,
if you have one, that is.
I do. Check this out.
What is this, some kind of joke?!
Even supermarket eggplants look
better than that old, lumpy,
beat-up thing!
Before you knock it, give it a taste.
Unless you're a "scaredy cat", of course.
It's... so... big.
Yeah, I'm shaking in my boots.
Sure does look good.
Yeah. Ms. Becky's eggplant
has started to let go of its moisture.
But Kei's hasn't changed at all.
And notice the size of those seeds.
Unlike yours truly, Kei's dish is disappointing
inside and out!
But you guys haven't tasted it yet.
All right then, here we go.
This is very delicious, Ms. Becky!
That just might be the best eggplant I've ever had!
Under-ripe. Just a little, though.
And the skin's too tough.
Obviously, you know nothing about eggplants,
that's how they're supposed to be!
All right then, time to give Kei's a try.
Eggplant!
Whoa. What the hell is he doing?!
Are you okay, sir?!
Now... That... Is... Tasty!
A delicious fruit packed
with a sense of immense accomplishment!
A scrumptious eggplant that will boldly go
where no eggplant has gone before!
Fresh and moist, though not watery.
A juicy morsel exploding with
flavor so smooth, so creamy,
you'll be on your knees begging for more!
A taste unlike any other taste
that has ever been before!
Sir, are you all right?
Yeah, that was insane.
Thank you very much.
That dish was truly a delectable triumph!
Mr. Kamatori. That, my dearest young man,
is an eggplant to rival all other eggplants!
My friend, you have to tell me,
where in the world did you find such a thing?
Well, as a matter of fact,
I grew it myself in my spare time.
Amazing.
But I must know, how's it so much better than the rest?
The seeds are my secret weapons.
I wish someone would plant their secret weapon
in my eggplant field!
See, the thing is...
My seeds are purebred.
They might look a little bit plain.
But with a touch of love and the proper care,
they will always retain their time-honored taste.
The reason those other eggplants
didn't satisfy your craving is...
they're F1 hybrid fakes.
Wait a sec. What?
First filial generation.
It's no big deal,
just a genetics term we plant guys use.
Bred for appearance first and taste second,
these first generation cultivars were created
for one reason alone: efficiency.
Efficiency?
This supreme focus on efficiency over quality
leads to the liberal use of chemical fertilizers
and pesticides on F1 products in an environment
that's as far from natural as you can get.
If that's not a bunch of manufactured crap,
then I don't know what is!
Hmm.
You do make an excellent point, Kamatori.
It's the truth, plain and simple, sir.
We have an elite educational summer program
that gives some of our more exemplary students
the unique opportunity to study
global agriculture abroad.
Miss Kochou Yoshida. Mister Kei Kamatori.
Would the two of you care to participate?
Well... Shall I do it?
Perhaps it might be worth a serious think.
Large-scale agriculture is flourishing overseas.
But, if Kei and I journey across the globe together,
people might mistakenly believe we're on our honeymoon.
Oh, what a delightful, and romantic,
comedy of errors that would be!
Thank you, but I'm not interested
in overseas agriculture.
I'm here to study small-scale, pesticide free,
organic farming based on the "eat local" concept,
not to learn the ins and outs of mass corporatization.
Excuse me.
You! You're here!
So are you. Well, what fortuitous luck.
You've saved me the trouble of having to summon you.
I do hope you've made your preparations.
What's wrong?
You okay?
Hey, I know this guy!
You were on "Sunrise on Gaia", weren't you?
You're President Menjou of Hexa Techs!
Hexa... what?
Hexa Techs is a massive company
that does everything from growing crops
to shipping them overseas.
It's the most successful produce company there is
and he runs it all!
So, that means Kei Kamatori is...
My unworthy son.
No! You're not my father! You're not anything to me!
Hmph. So, you're his teacher I take it?
Yes, and available!
Please begin the process of
transferring my son out of here!
Like, very available!
Gather up your things. You're not to waste time
wallowing in a place like this a moment longer.
How dare you?
What do you mean a "place like this"?
Ah. Ringo.
Answer me. What exactly does that mean?
This school is the best.
In all of...  I was going to say Japan,
but I really think this school grows
the most delicious vegetables in the whole world.
"The most delicious vegetables in the whole world"?
Um. What is so amusing?
Well, I'll give her this much:
for a lowly ag-school student,
she does have a strong imagination.
Like you're one to talk with
that F1 manufactured garbage
you call produce, you jerk!
You've got quite the lip on you,
but would you be willing to put
your money where your mouth is?
I'll gladly take you on any day, old man.
If that's the case, how about a showdown?
Bring it.
I propose a simple match:
your vegetables versus mine.
Whoever sells the most product wins.
I do have one stipulation. If I manage to beat you
fair and square, you'll stay out of agriculture forever.
All right. But if you lose, you leave this school.
And never come back!
Good luck.
I haven't shown this to anyone yet.
But this is where I'm raising my purebred vegetables.
So, this is where you've been running off to
when you disappear for hours on end.
Geez, you're taking care of all of this by yourself?
Yeah. Bringing back heirloom vegetables
is a deep passion of mine.
Unlike my father...
The only thing he cares about is lining his pockets.
Quality doesn't matter to him at all!
Hey, Kei. I'm confused, if Menjou's your real last name,
then how come you go by Kamatori?
Kamatori is my aunt's name.
I asked her to adopt me, and she did.
You're adopted?
But why forsake your name?
'Cause my stupid father is a despicable human being!
At the end of the day, he's just a guy in a suit.
He has no real love for agriculture.
All he cares about is business.
So, is that the real reason why you didn't want to go
into that study abroad program, because of your father?
I love farming. And I'm here because it's important,
even if it is on a small scale.
I refuse to end up like him.
Back home, we tended a melon farm.
Without chemical fumigation,
melons are often prone to pests,
and let me tell you, our farm wasn't
without its share of issues on that front.
But the problem was, my mother was
very sensitive to these chemicals.
That didn't stop him from using them though,
his eye always fixated on the bottom line.
How awful.
Even after they killed his own wife,
he still uses those chemicals.
Because when all's said and done,
profit matters to him more than
anything else in this world.
Even his own family!
I'm sorry. But if that's not a prime example
of why all farms should operate chemical-free,
then I don't know what is.
Look, this is a lot to ask.
And I know I shouldn't get
you involved in this showdown.
But the truth is, I really do need your help!
We're here for you, Kei. What do you say, you guys?
Sure! Done!
What I mean is, from a personal stand-point,
I have no reason to care whether Kei Kamatori
has to leave us behind.
But for the sake of Tamo-No Rin,
we cannot afford to lose him!
We'll show that old fart of a want to-be farmer
who really runs things around here!
What do you think about that, Ringo?
He's going down.
We'll wipe the floor with his dumb face!
Thanks, everyone.
Whoever sells the most product in one hour wins,
plain and simple.
Just to clarify, you mean sales, not profit, correct?
Yes, that's right.
But we have the same amount of market space.
You can try to boost sales by selling at a loss
but it won't work.
I know that, I'm not an imbecile.
If I were in your shoes, I'd worry about myself.
Right. First thing we need to do is set some prices.
Whatever his prices are, we'll match them.
Huh?
My vegetables are organic and pesticide free.
Taste will win the day!
Well, look at what the cat dragged in.
Whoa. What the heck are you doing here?!
I came to help you.
Look: If you want to sell some vegetables
and be filthy stinking rich,
then all you have to do is use
Class D's Ace Sales Technique.
You'll leave ol' daddy dearest in the dust!
What's that sprayer for?
Watch and learn.
Incredible! They look amazing!
Freshly picked, and covered top
to bottom in sweet morning dew!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Visit the parking lot now
for a limited-time-only fresh vegetable market!
All right! Let's get out there and sell, sell, sell!
Yeah!
It looks like it's pretty fresh.
But it does have a very unusual shape.
And worms have been at it.
Yes, and that's proof of its organic,
pesticide-free upbringing.
If you don't believe me, have a taste!
Well. I suppose that's why the bugs like it.
I'm sold!
Thanks a lot for shopping with us today!
Excellent. So far, there hasn't been
too much action at Hexa Techs.
Plus, I'm just getting started over here.
Time to seal the deal!
Yes, ma'am!
Hey! What the heck are they doing?!
Relax, my friend, have a look.
What is this?
It's just a little trick I call, "merchandising."
"Merchan-dising"?
Listen up. It's midsummer, right?
And it's Friday, the start of a relaxing weekend.
And you know what that means.
Actually, I don't.
It means lots of people with cash to spare
want to get out there and live it up a little.
And what's the easiest way to accomplish that feat?
Sleep?
Yakiniku, obviously!
Korean barbeque!
Hey, look at that, they have yakiniku!
That's a great way to get our veggies in!
Merchandising is quite simple, really.
It's all about providing the right product.
In the perfect amount at the exact right price.
At precisely the right moment
when people need what you're selling.
You guys, this is too much!
It's like she's so freaking smart
my head is gonna explode!
It looks like the only extras
they have are free samples.
I really think we can win! He's behind, isn't he?
I mean, we've had a ton more customers.
Still. We can do way better.
Whoa, you mean you've got something else up your sleeve?
Advertising, friends! Sales promotions!
It's like they always say:
"You can sell anything with sex."
Guys! It's boner jam time!
"We like veg-gies. They're racy. They're lacy.
They're tasty.
Don't you want to put them in your mouth?!"
Hey!
Oh, come on, Lady,
you can't stay embarrassed about this forever!
Right. Now let's get walking!
Is everybody eating their vegetables?
Yeah!
Their voices, youth, charm,
and undeniable attractiveness
catch the customer's eye while
subconsciously making them
more eager to spend their money on your product.
Plus this.
In order to attract the ever-important male demographic,
these pretty ladies come with Nestletix, too!
Hold on. What?
You can ask any girl you like
to put any veggie you want between her breasts.
Whoa! Amazing. That's an incredible strategy!
To compete with Hexa Techs' sheer brand power,
"the gloves" are gonna have to come off,
or in the case of these ladies, "the bras."
You're so smart... So, uh...
Any girl?
Uh. Like this?
Oh yeah! We hit the jackpot!
Now it's our turn to have some fun!
Holy crap, what the heck are you doing?
Why are you here?!
We came to show that snake in a suit
what a proper peasant uprising is like!
Plus, I hear his dad's a total silver fox.
All four of them representing in full force!
I'll help.
Anything for one of the most
talented students in school.
But sweet Kei, call me "Mom."
Please!
Go on, give it a try!
Come on, big boy, there's nothing to be nervous about!
That's right, sugar tits, call me your naughty mama!
Who's your naughty mama, huh?! Who's your hot mama?!
Come on, give mommy a big,
wet smooch right on the old kisser,
preferably with tongue!
Let's get her!
I'm on it!
Stop squirming!
Let me go!
Damn you! Stop it!
Let me out! Let! Me! Out!
Come and eat our veggies!
Just look at this delightfully scrumptious eggplant
nestling between her two gigantic fun bags!
Ugh. Marketing is so beneath me.
Whatever, it works like a charm every time.
Hang in there, Boobs, you'll make it through this.
"Boobs"?! Don't call me that!
Check us out, ladies!
Huh?
So. Want to take a bite of my eggplant?
Or would you like to munch on my big cuke?
Or, my tomatoes?!
Someone let me outta here right now!
I have crops to harvest!
All that work, and in the end,
we still couldn't even come close to competing
with the Hexa Techs brand.
So is that the reason you beat us,
'cause people have heard of Hexa Techs before?!
That's not it.
What?!
Give it a try.
You too.
It tastes good.
It does. Really good.
What?! But how?! How can that be?!
You've poo-poo'd our vegetables from the very beginning,
and even agreed on a head-to-head showdown
without so much as even tasting what we have to offer.
Do you know what that makes you, Kei?
A naïve little brat!
Answer me this:
how many hours do you devote
to your vegetables every day?
One hour? Two? Five, perhaps six at most?
We at Hexa Techs attend to our vegetables
24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
You students, with your little farming hobby,
could never compete with the superiority of our product!
Fine. Spin it however you want,
but all you're really doing is manipulating F1s
and you know it!
Hexa Techs embraces technology, is that so abominable?
Do you really believe that vegetables
raised by nature alone are somehow nobler
than those that have been researched and improved
by scientific methods? Tell me: do you intend
to rewrite the very history of agriculture?
No, I just...
Look, what I'm trying to say is...
It's vulgar. Everything you do is for money, that's all.
The truth is, I've absolutely no respect for you!
Our product is safer. Far less expensive!
And above all else, tastes better!
So tell me:
Where's the vulgarity in what I do? Eh?!
It's called progress!
You fool! That remark of yours
belittles not only agricultural workers,
but it's also an
insult to the consumer!
No. That's not true.
Everything I fight for is for the good of the consumer.
You-You're dead wrong.
I keep my vegetables organic
and pesticide-free for them!
You still don't get it, do you?
You're just imposing your own shallow,
unilateral idealism onto them.
Can you grow delicious vegetables
without chemicals and pesticides?
To grow truly tasty, delectable vegetables,
you need high-level farming techniques
and the commensurate experience.
And last I checked, you had neither.
But at Hexa Techs we have plenty.
So brand recognition isn't the only reason you lost.
I've failed. It's over!
I'm a man of my word... So take me where you will!
No. Actually, I've changed my mind.
You what?!
I can't let my company fail in the hands
of a successor that cares only to grow paltry crops.
You are free to do as you wish.
I don't understand!
You want to win? Then find a realistic method
to grow better vegetables than your old man.
I hope the study abroad program
gives you what you need!
If I don't get to know my enemy,
how can I ever hope to defeat him?
And besides, I really should see
what this world has to offer.
I'm a little worried that you-know-who
hasn't shown up yet.
Yeah, where is Boobs?
Have no fear, Kochou's here!
Oh, wow.
The little princess looks like a bride
about to leave for her honeymoon.
No, no, no, no, no, you're wrong!
I resent the implication!
What you see here is nothing more than proper etiquette!
You country bumpkins know nothing of the chic world
of international travel.
Umm. Come along, Kei Kamatori.
Right.
Well, I guess it's time to go.
Yep. You guys be careful.
Woo! Bring me something awesome!
See you later, guys.
Cheerful Farming Village.