Oh, I see...
You want to know if the new transfer
is the girl of your dreams, eh?
Adorable.
Wait for it...
Miss Becky!
It's not so simple as yes or no.
Please, you're killing us!
So, Yukatan.
That is who you are, right?
You'll have to excuse him.
What he means is, you're that singer chick, right?
Not really.
Why you slumming it in this dive?
I don't know.
Uh, all-righty then.
Truth is:
The new girl was pop sensation Yuka Kusakabe,
but now she goes by Ringo Kinoshita.
Called it!
Not so fast!
Huh?
It's safe to assume she enrolled here under a
new name to put the billboard days behind her.
Ah. I get it.
So, no bringing up her past then.
Right.
But...
Come on!
Don't translate that to mean "avoid her
altogether." The poor dear needs help adjusting!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You want us to help this Ringo,
whatever-her-name is, fit in? It'll be perfect!
She's in the same dorm as you all.
What?
Plus you have the same major
and you're in the same class.
Oh, wow. How intelligent of me!
Let me get this straight:
We'll be attached at the hip?
So, like, on the farm?
And-And in the classroom?
And where 'at the hip' can be taken literally?!
I'm dreaming this, aren't I?
No, it's real.
Nosebleed!
Pleased to meet you, Miss Yukata... !
Uh, sorry, I mean: Miss Kinoshita.
Ha. I'm Kousaku Hata, so, uh, hi.
Right, right.
Give me a sec.
This is my friend. Wakadanna.
Or... Young Master.
Anyway.
Let me be the first to welcome you to Tamo
No-Rin, where everyone's a team player!
Is he talking like a recruiter or is it just me?
Um, I think he's trying to sound smart.
Tour-time!
There'll be a quiz afterwards-not really.
This is the main building.
Classes are divided up by department.
Here we have the gym.
The complex of buildings to our
right has kind of a tricky name.
We call it the Industrial Promotion Building.
Bit of a mouthful, huh?
There's the Green Shop, like the sign says.
That's where we sell all of our vegetables and stuff.
I know.
Uh... Ah, cool.
A cat?
Uh...
No, that'd be a peacock.
It's so drab.
Oh. Right, I get you.
See when we think of a peacock, we think of the males.
In nature, it's the guys who
have to deck themselves out.
Girls are... Drab.
Nice move, doofus! You're losing her!
This is the Wallaby House.
It's where Wakadana lives.
Heated flooring, AC...
It's actually a lot nicer than our dorms.
So, Wakadana's not a kangaroo?
Well, they are similar, but not quite the same.
So, uh...
Yeah.
If you're interested, I could tell you about how
Wakadana and me became buddies back in the day.
He didn't used to be attached to us.
But then one night, actually,
it was Christmas just last year.
Either 'cause he was tired of being cooped up
or just couldn't sleep, the little fella got out
and wandered around in the snow until, well,
until it got to be too much for him.
Luckily, I was wandering
around myself and found him.
Took him to my room as fast as I could.
He slept cuddled up next to me inside my...
Uh... Inside a big pillowcase.
We've been pals ever since.
When he gets bored,
he comes over to hang out with me and the gang.
Pretty heartwarming story, huh?
Continuing the tour!
Feast your eyes on that!
That's what quality poultry looks
like when it's too good for plebeians!
The three breeds of locally raised poultry are:
Hinai, Nagoya Cochin, and the superlative Satsuma.
Less famous, perhaps, but of equal merit is the
poultry raised here in our very own Gifu prefecture
submitted for your unqualified appraisal.
Very nice. Let's eat!
Well done. Thank you.
Why...
Don't speak to me as though my self-esteem as an
animal husbandry specialist hinges on your approval!
Consider yourself blessed that I deign
to let you sample my wares at all!
She's so mean. Why?
I beg your pardon?!
If you're trying to insinuate that I have unrequited
feelings for Kei, you're barking up the wrong tree!
That's not to suggest I haven't
a modicum of respect for the man.
But I regard him primarily as a rival!
Uh, any chance I can have some eggs?
Vulgarian...
Let me ask you.
Between fertilized and unfertilized,
which kind of egg is more, I guess, you know,
better for you?
Moron!
How do you call yourself an
Ag Major and sleep at night?!
Nutritionally, there is no difference between the two.
That said, let there be no question that eggs produced
by caged fowl, when compared to those produced
by the free-range variety,
are enormously less delectable.
Sorry. Thanks for explaining.
Hey.
"Unfertilized egg" means what?
Look.
I'm from the city, okay?
I don't know the first thing about eggs.
Wow, that is seriously adorable!
This stuff is so... boring.
No!
Anyway...
Unfertilized, means?
Well, I, uh...
Give me a sec to explain!
Okay, I'm not going to lie:
I don't even know where to start on this one.
What are you talking about?
You know this: just start from the beginning.
Look at her! She's too delicate!
This is down and dirty stuff she's asking about.
I can't just go there.
Oh, spare me! It's a clinical matter.
Be clinical. The principle's the same for plants.
Think, pistil and stamen.
What I think is that she ought
to hear it from another girl.
Fine!
Behold, rookie!
Yeah?
If you would, madam.
Your undivided attention.
Yes!
An unfertilized egg is essentially
an egg wearing a condom!
The first order of business when it
comes to Agriculture is record keeping.
That's the last time I ask Fun
Bags to explain anything to anyone.
Sweetie, you've heard the phrase "putting
all your eggs in one basket," yes?
Fertilizing them?
No, not exactly.
What I'm getting at here is the
importance of playing fast and loose!
What the experts say about the same-old, same-old is
true. For example: When a grown man practices monogamy.
Yeah, right.
His wife...
Whoa, there!
Kind of an inappropriate example, don't you think?
What? She's a girl. She needs to know.
You might be going off on a tangent.
The point I'm getting at is,
when we re-use the same soil year after
year, eventually the crop won't take.
The concept is known as replant failure.
Simple as that.
Huh?
Replant failure! Simple as that!
Yes. Thank you! Awesome!
If you'll excuse me, I'd like to propose a toast.
As dorm leader, it's my privilege to
welcome Miss Kinoshita into the fold.
We're very happy to
Dang it, guys!
I vote we stuff our faces! Heh.
There's really not a whole heck of a
lot to do in a po-dunk town like this.
But, there's enough fresh grub to feed an army!
This is way too much for me.
Oh. Well...
Is it just me, or is she being kind of bitchy?
Come on! Give her chance.
She's probably just nervous. Wouldn't you be?
Maybe, but either way, you wouldn't be the
only human being I bothered talking to.
Heh heh! Ah... You noticed that, huh?
Ugh. Please! Idiot.
Her attitude's not exactly going to help her fit in.
Look, if your girlfriend wants to cut it
here, she needs to learn how to play ball!
Huh. Guess you have a point.
What you need to do is stop fan-boying long
enough to set an example. Quit trying to schmooze,
and get her familiar with how things work.
I know that, I'm just... I'm establishing trust.
Who wants to see an impression?
Ha! Yeah!
Helium-filled sex doll.
Woo-hoo!
I have daddy issues.
Woo-hoo...
Yeah... Woo-hoo...
All right, then. Another one.
I give you "cock of the walk!"
Nope!
Overreact there much, chief?
No more impressions! It's game time!
In fact, why don't we let the new
girl pick what she'd like to play?
Uh...
How about "Who's the King?"
Huh?
Red straw's the King!
Ha-ha! The red one's mine!
Kei's got one. Pretty sure that
signal means Minori has three.
Yes! This is my chance!
As King, I command whoever has
Number Two to feed me by hand!
Oh. Glad that's not weird.
Damn it! How did you end up with Number Two?!
I'm not any happier about it than you are!
I was trying to signal you that Ringo had three.
if it'd been a snake, it would've bit you!
Your secret code is stupid!
Quit stalling and play the game.
The King asked to be fed.
Your Highness...
Ahh...
Heh...
Glad we're not playing spin-the-bottle, huh?
Sorry...
Red straw's the King!
Tee-hee.
Yes. Exactly as planned.
As king, I command Number Three
to step on my face barefoot!
Ugh. Is something wrong with you or do you just hate me?
No!
I... hate my life!
If you're going to signal me, be consistent!
Uh-uh, don't pin this one on me!
Did you or did you not say my
secret code was stupid last time?
Whatever, just do it!
Step on my face!
You really need to see a therapist at some point.
Let's get this over with...
Do it quick.
I don't know what this is doing
for you and I don't need to know.
Let's just agree never to speak of this again.
You're a good sport, Minori. Heh.
You know what they say, "the more you stomp
it, the bigger the barley grows."
Nobody says that.
Okay, that's enough!
Right. That looked bad.
But... I swear!
Sorry...
Red straw's the King!
Looks like it's me.
Oh. Yay.
It's you.
Huh. Nice...
Uh, is something the matter?
No, I'm good.
What're you?
Huh?
What number do you have?
I can't just tell you! That takes the fun out of it.
Eh! Uhm... One. But this is against the rules.
Number One has to call me by my first name.
You... You'd be okay with that?
I mean, we only just met.
It's Ringo, by the way.
Yeah... I-I know.
Good.
Call me that from now on.
Ringo. Nice "ring" to it. Heh.
What the... ?! Oh no!
Morning, Waka. Oh, that's right: it's Sunday.
More playtime.
Man. Wait 'til you get a load of the dream I had.
Last night, I thought Yuka transferred here from Tokyo
and was totally putting the moves on me
while we were playing "Who's the Ki... ".
What?
Nothing!
Just thinking about how awesome Ghibli is, you know?
What are you doing?
Laundry.
Ah... I see.
What?
Uh... Nothing! Ha!
So, if you're having trouble figuring this monster out,
and it is complicated, I could help?
I can do it on my own, thank you. But if you want.
Right.
Look, the first thing you need to learn is how to ask.
Nevermind.
I'll wash them in the river.
Look, I don't know what they teach you in
the concrete jungle, but we're rustic here,
not Neanderthal. We'll use the washing machine!
First thing we do is separate colors from delicates.
Oohh...
"Delicate" means "white," basically.
Everything else is "color."
After that, we divvy up by material.
Go on, I believe in you!
Here goes!
Wait! Are you cool with me watching you do this?
Huh?
It's just, you know,
I'm seeing your underwear and all!
You embarrassed?
Heck no! But, I mean, aren't you?
Whatever, I'm a modern guy!
If it's fine by you, it's fine by me.
Which pile do these go into?
Ah. Panties.
Technically, you could go either way.
Uh... 'cause they're color!
And delicate!
What do we do?
Hand-wash.
Seriously?
Yup.
Washing machine would be way too rough on them.
Then again, if you've never hand-washed
something before, it can be challenging.
You think so? Really?
Oh yeah. Fortunately for you,
I'm experienced with these things.
I'd be happy to help! Come to daddy!
Come to daddy, my precious.
I am so going to OD!
Step away from the unmentionables, you pervert!
So close...
Ugh! Leave the poor girl alone!
Like it or not, a woman has the
right to launder her undies in peace!
Wait. He's not doing anything wrong.
I just asked for his help with my clothes.
I couldn't figure out the washing machine, okay?
Look, take my word for it, I know the guy:
he's a ticking time bomb.
I've earned the right to say that
'cause I've put up with his creeper man-games
since we were kids, alright?
You've known the perv for, what? A whole day?
Oh, I'm sorry, I called your man a "perv."
What the hell is your problem?
Me?
Yes, you.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Okay, okay I like a good catfight
as much as the next guy,
but this is getting on my nerves!
Stop being a queen bee and give her panties back!
Every second you have them in your paws
they drop in purity by a whole order of magnitude!
You're saying I'm impure?!
Bravo! Give the girl a prize!
Once upon a time, men wrote hymns
to underwear this wholesome!
Thunder pants like yours- they burned at the stake!
Ah... Wow. Nice one.
You really put these panties on a
pedestal, huh? Unbelievable.
Just shut up and hand them over!
Wait. I have a better idea.
I'll go you one better.
You... If you...
If you want them, hers and mine are a package deal!
Ew! Gross!
Oh, you have got to be kidding me!
Don't be such a drama queen!
If you're going to force me to take
your skid-marked parachute undies,
at least hand me the snow white pair first!
Parachute undies...?
Quit bitching and give them here!
Ha! Over my dead body!
Nope!
If all you're going to do is fight over
them, just give them back to me.
Could everyone calm down, please?
This is stupid. I heard everything.
You should all be ashamed!
Clearly, there's only one way
to settle this issue properly.
Excuse me? Like how?
We test your expertise!
It's like looking into the sun!
Here's the deal: pick the
highest quality pair of panties
from the selection you see here, and you win.
Winner gets two things: my undying respect,
and bragging rights as the foremost
authority on ladies' undies.
Hmm...
These look pretty swanky.
Cute. Totally what I would have picked.
Great minds think alike, huh?
Right.
I'm going with these 'cause they're
what I'd choose to wear myself.
Ha! Read them and weep, loser-boy!
I was f...king with you.
C'mon, that's not how the game is played!
Us girls got to stick together!
Whatever, these are absolutely the ones!
You know jack about quality.
At the end of the day,
it's not about cuteness or comfort.
Oh. Is that a fact?
Nice try, Kei,
but your little setup here doesn't fool me.
I... choose none!
Not a single pair on this table has ever been worn!
Oh...? Huh?
Guys couldn't care less about
sheer fabric or frilly little bows.
They care about whether or not the panties have
ever gotten down and dirty in the trenches!
Unworn pairs of ladies'
undergarments are a dime a dozen!
Hmph!
Well, who am I to argue the basic economics with a
man who'd give his left nut to sniff a used pair?
In most cases, the reverse is true, but with panties,
used versus unused can mean the difference between
several decimal points.
But what we're actually talking about
isn't the panties themselves.
But the sexual commodification of the wearer!
If you would hand me the pair
you have in your hands, please.
Sure. There's no question who's the expert.
You've, definitely earned these.
Ah-ha! Yeah!
Get ready, nose!
Sorry! You've lost, pal!
I'll bet you thought those belonged to Kinoshita.
But they're mine!
They... They're what?!
I've had them bunched up under my
armpit for the past five minutes.
That's right.
Nobody said anything to anyone
about them being your dream girl's.
These, on the other hand!
So I basically just buried my nose in your...
Afraid so.
How could you?
I thought you were my friend?
You've tricked me! Why?
What have I done to deserve this...?
This was all on purpose!
Bastard! You knew exactly what you were doing!
You've turned this laundry room into a den of lies!
C'mon, man get a grip, already.
Let this be a lesson to you that not all used panties
have seen the kind of trenches you're interested in.
Then tell me....
How's a man supposed to judge quality?
There's no surefire way.
Value is in the eye of the beholder.
Why do you sound like a guru all of a sudden?
I don't understand.
Consider this:
Stop thinking in terms of the panties themselves.
The only pair worth its weight
in gold is the pair unseen.
The one thing we're drawn to without fail is mystery.
Once we've seen them they're
just a run-o'-the-mill fact.
What they are is nothing
compared to what they represent.
That's really deep...
So, one in the hand is...
Is worth none in the bush.
Wow, I... I was jerk.
Sorry I threw them away.
I didn't understand their panty power.
Nah, I was the jerk.
I didn't understand any better than you.
There, that's the spirit.
Glad you two remember how to be friends.
Since my work's done,
I'll be taking Kinoshita's panties for myself.
What?!
You dirty double-crossing... !
Stop belly-aching! You already have your own!
Huh? What are you talking about?
The ones in your heart...
Of course!
They've been with me from the beginning!
Everyone carries their own high-quality pair
of ladies' unmentionables in their heart!
Guys! Let's hang these up like banners and have a party!
A Spring-line Panties Party!
I'll make my special red rice!
Yo, sweetheart... you in or you out?
You guys are all idiots!
And so our Spring-Line Panties Party ended.
About five seconds after it started.
But, man, it was fun!
"Super Sub-Mom War: Training Stage"