Moe Eggs!
Farm fresh, unfertilized and unbelievably smooth!
Cooked or raw.
Yum! So very tasty!
Where else can you get eggs likes this
but--you guessed it--Tamo No-Rin High School?
Our eggs use condoms, so you know they're safe!
Sure, that last part was bit much,
but, hey, we had an idea and we ran with it.
None of us knew it would be the proverbial golden goose.
Moe rice.
Any clue what I'm talking about?
Yeah, no.
Oh-ho! You've got to see it!
They've been all over the news!
Very simple concept.
Rice with a hot naked lady on
the packaging sells like wow!
Step one: Produce. Step two: Sex.
Step three: Cash.
It's actually real.
Wow. Really?
They hired a manga artist.
I forget his name,
but he's real popular with the otaku crowd.
He drew a bishojo chick in a tantalizing pose and boom.
Thirty-two tons of rice sold online in ninety days.
The company normally unloads about fifteen tons a year,
so the new mascot earned them eight times
their average monthly sales.
Whoa! Damn!
Imagine how much we can sell
if we took the same approach?!
A little tasteful nudity and the
school would be rolling in it!
I smell profit. Ah, hello my lovelies.
Heads up! We've got a Top Four!
Whenever two or more people talk finance,
this one's ready to pounce! Hide your 401k's!
Hmm... So, she's a Top Four?
Correct! The school has four of these types in all.
One: Fun Bags Yoshida from Class A.
Two: Bio Suzuki from Class B.
Three: Woodman Rintarou from Class F.
Rose Hanazono from Class E.
And last but not least, from Class D,
agronomic specialist and marketing-slash-logistics guru,
Money Kanegami!
Hmm... You just named five.
Never mind about that!
So... Rolling in it, huh?
Something we can help you with?
All we've been through together
and that's how you say hello?
Thought I counted for more than that.
Didn't your recent hedge fund shenanigans
get you indefinitely suspended?
Oh, they let me back in as of yesterday.
But let's cut to the chase. You're cooking something up.
Mama wants in.
Good for you.
The Moe racket's a cash cow.
I've been wanting to dip my wick
into that honey pot for ages.
Yeah, well, easier said than done.
it's not exactly low-hanging fruit.
He's right, you know.
We'd need a big name artist onboard.
Anybody can slap a pic of some spread-eagle bimbo
on the front of a rice bag and use it to boost sales.
You want a big-name artiste, then here you go.
It doesn't get much bigger than the
illustrator for Kippu, ladies ann germs.
He's available, he's interested,
and he's in my contacts.
What?!
When you say Kippu, you mean THE Kippu?!
None other.
You mean that one guy who does all
those light novel illustrations?!
That's him.
The genius who draws all the critically acclaimed
pinup girl artwork?!
Indeed.
The same dude who fell from grace with the art community
not long ago for manga-fying some lameass story about
Ag students and whose family threatened to cut him off
if he didn't rethink his career choices?!
Yes, I think we all know it is.
And he's sincerely interested?
Well he is a professional.
If the price is right,
I think we should consider him sincere.
He's worth every penny, I can assure you.
Wow. You hear that?
That's the sound of us actually having a shot at this!
Lend me a hand, my lovelies,
and I just might be able to make it worth your while.
Huh. Lend you a hand? What do you want us to do?
Look at me.
I'm not exactly in the yearbook
as "most trustworthy," now am I?
But if I had fine, upstanding students
like yourselves to vouch for me...
We could get this thing off the ground.
Ahh... So we're your bargaining chip.
I completely understand!
Kousaku would be more than happy to help!
Don't volunteer me!
Look, this is simple risk management.
If Kanegami runs afoul of anti-trust laws
and the school needs a scapegoat,
somebody needs to stay behind with the shredder.
Why does it get to be you?
Basic question: What are we planning to sell?
I'd say damn near anything given this guy's talent.
A drawing of his could sell ice to Eskimos.
Now, we got to balance supply and demand,
so think stable inventory.
Best branding in the world isn't going to do us
a whole lot of good if there's
nothing to package, right?
Gotcha.
The trick is to sell something
we have constant access to.
Something with a yield we can rely on.
I've got just the thing.
Excellent choice.
Oh yeah, those!
We have a winner.
Um, okay?
Out of the question!
C'mon, don't be like that!
They're perfect!
Your eggs are made for the big time and you know it!
Ugh! Disgusting! Moe eggs! Please!
The very idea induces apoplexy!
Producers with integrity compete
on the merit of their product.
Period.
Is it lonely up there on your high horse?
This is no different in principle than selling them
at the Green Shop.
Look, they're still being touted on their merits.
We're just helping those merits
reach a larger market share.
Ah! So it's you! Why am I not surprised?
Do we or don't we owe it to ourselves and the school
to cast our net as widely as possible?
And I suppose next you'll lecture me on
laissez faire capitalism!
Don't think I don't know what you're up to, madam!
D'aw. Please. Why be so reactive, doll?
Take a moment to give me a fair hearing.
Whatever I'm "up to" here, the end game is this:
your eggs becoming a household name.
Well...
I have to admit, they are certainly worthy.
Just imagine...
Think about it.
A carton in every kitchen in Japan.
You know, I can't think of another farmer
for whom that's true.
But we've always prided ourselves
on the "locally produced" label.
Won't our regular clientele feel betray--
Sweetheart, listen.
You've heard the horror stories.
Feed laced with hormones and antibiotics.
Unsanitary living conditions.
Now, haven't the corporate farms had their shot?
Hasn't the public been subjected
to their "anything to fatten
the bottom-line" ideology long enough?
C'mon, take your place in the sun.
This isn't about money!
Oh, no. It's about consumer rights!
Please! Do the right thing!
Y-Yes. The system can work.
We can make it work. I believe in us!
--I... --Game, set, match.
Damn she's good.
Okey-doke! The product is Moe Eggs.
The mascot is Aleggsis. We brand aggressively.
Come on! Let me hear you!
Woo-hoo!
So... How we doing?
Not so bad. People seem to like the blog.
Great! Post the four-panel manga!
How's the print media campaign?
Just bought space in three issues of a top anime mag!
Hello. Moe Eggs.
Yes. Yes.
Just one moment.
Someone wants the figurine copyright!
Huh? Okay. That was fast.
Heh. They're falling over themselves.
Hmm... Now what?
They want to use it for an event?
I say let them have the copyright.
We're an LLC, so the risk is on them.
Either way, it's free exposure.
That's the ticket!
Kei! Give them the go!
Roger.
Moe Eggs!
They like it when you peel them a little rough.
So wet and slippery...
Go on... No one's looking.
You deserve the very best!
Thank you for calling Moe Eggs.
No, sorry.
We're not accepting any more preorders at this time.
Yeah, that's right: as advertised.
Order now and your shipment will get there in 90 days.
Okay. This is getting out of hand.
Bad news.
The school server's down. Too many orders!
Aw, man. This is the last thing we need!
Oh, no. They'll start burning up the phones.
Alright, that settles it.
We need a phone bank in here, STAT.
First things first.
We've got to get these packed up and shipped!
Right, right. Man, we need more hands.
Got anybody we can bring in on this?
Sell my little porcelain orbs, sell!
Look, I'm telling you: twins are the way to go.
Perfect choice for branding double-yolk eggs.
I say yes.
I'm leaning toward "Hard-Boiled Shelly"
and "Ramona Ramekin."
Ooh, I like that! Plays up their versatility!
Bad news. I think We have a graphics issue.
What in the name of...?
What is that?!
Gross! She's old enough to be my mom!
I thought we were all in agreement to go Lolita.
I, uh, think there's been a misunderstanding.
This is not good, people!
Older women have their charms.
Th-They do?
Call her experienced.
She's a shoe-in for the soft-boiled line.
Ooh!
Make it happen!
Aye-aye, sir!
Throw up a teaser on the website!
All over it!
I want out.
Eh? Why? We're kicking ass!
I'll be honest with you: I
don't like where we're headed.
Just look at us.
Don't you resent having to fall
back on cheap marketing tricks?
It's about exposure, man.
How else are our eggs going
to compete in a global market?
Or don't you believe in our product?
As usual, you've put the cart before the horse.
Oh, I'm putting the cart before the horse?
How about you think outside the box?!
Hah. Whatever, man.
Have fun playing corporate tycoon.
Giddyup, Jun.
Heeyah!
Kei, wait!
Ugh. He's going to break that poor thing's back.
You've heard the hype,
you probably have a carton of
her eggs in your refrigerator.
Now hear first-hand from the chicken lady herself
whose business went from modest to Moe
in a mindboggling matter of weeks,
whether or not there's a correlation between
egg consumption and cup size.
Well organically produced eggs
are a good source of protein,
so it's reasonable to posit a relationship-- Ugh!
I did not agree to debase myself!
She sure has become a celebrity.
Yeah, the camera adores her.
Did you ever think the company would take off like this?
I don't know. Maybe.
I mean, I figured we'd do well-- Whoops.
There. Don't want the meat to catch fire.
You want intestines a little crispy, but not well done.
When the fat's crackling,
that's the sign to move it off the heat.
Voila.
That's a new one to me.
Oh, nice! Absolutely perfect!
It's a good metaphor for business.
When it's cooked to perfection, you're done.
You've got to know when to move on.
It's the difference between a gourmand and a pyromaniac.
Huh.
So what's next on the board for Moe Eggs?
That's the point I'm trying to make.
Moe Eggs is a thing of the past.
What? But, we...
Local farmers will buy the trademark.
The school will make a killing.
And we move on to other things. All for the best really.
Our business venture has been a shot in the arm
for the local economy.
We're selling out?
Well, sort of. But we won't reap a profit.
Students aren't legally allowed to exploit the school
for personal gain. You do know that, right?
Hang on--!
Easy now, Rockefeller.
Ag training's not about making
returns on the produce we grow.
It's about learning how to make returns.
Think of it like a financial laboratory.
Now's the time for experimentation,
not portfolio building.
Which is great, 'cause once we're out in the real world,
we won't have the safety nets we have here.
We mess up, we make bad business choices...
We're on our own.
See, kid. There'll be plenty of time to amass
our fortunes once we've graduated.
For the moment, the trick is to
take advantage of our freedom.
A gourmand enjoys a dish cooked to perfection.
A pyro just ends up getting burned.
Kanegami.
Yeah?
Well. I don't really know how to put this.
I guess I always thought your whole MO was making money.
Don't get me wrong.
Money's all that and a bag of chips, no lie.
But it's far from the be-all-end-all, trust me.
Thing is, when push comes to shove, I crave adventure.
Passion. Sure, money can make that happen,
but it's not the end goal.
It's a tool. That's all.
Wow, that's deep.
Right. So. Eggs are old news.
But, there are plenty of other markets to tap.
Such as?
Heh... Clearly the next logical step is yaoi.
The B in Class B stands for Boy Love!
Nice of you to finally put
in an appearance, Akari.
Garcon! Warm glass of milk, please! No ice cubes!
What's going on?
The otaku market is setting its
sights on the female dollar.
Women are dropping more cash on sex
merch than their male counterparts.
Maybe the modern woman has become lonesome.
Whatever the case, only a fool would ignore the trend.
Yeah, I get it. But, what's our product?
Try to stay with me, chief:
you know the fungal culture practicum from Class F?
You mean those grubby old logs they
use to cultivate shiitake and shimeji
and other crap like that?
Think about it, kiddo. You're a fungi, am I right?
What does that even mean?
Look, I got to be honest. Mushrooms sorta gross me out.
Oh calm down, reverend. It's not the 'shrooms I'm after,
it's the logs those little fellas are cultivated on.
The market's screaming for one.
Wait. Really?
The branding creates itself.
The hell are you?! Crazy?!
Try to be objective for a moment, please.
The demand-side definitely has an upper limit.
It'll be a cash-grab pure and simple, you dig?
We'll adopt a hit-and-run strategy
that'll maximize our market impact.
I, uh... think you might be taking things too...
Hey, Suzuki, I could use a little help any time now.
You know what'd be perfect?
A little dab of yogurt on the tip.
I am not comfortable with this!
Cross promotion!
We could say "apply Class B yogurt
for mushrooms bigger than your wildest dreams!"
You know what?
That's just insane enough to work.
This is gonna be huge.
I ought to put an axe through your skull!
Yeah, I know, right?
What do you say we go to the roof.
Just you and me.
'Cause I really feel like teaching somebody how to fly.
Maybe some other time, that's not why I'm here.
I thought you'd be interested in
showing off Class F's mad skills.
Very funny. Good one, man.
You think we train as hard as
we do to help make pornography?
Believe me, I'm as uncomfortable as you.
No worries, dude. I get it. It's too weird.
I should've seen this coming.
But could you at least have a look at it
and tell me whether or not it's possible?
Fine. Technically it couldn't be easier.
You drill yourself a big enough
hole, stick in the spores,
and then there's fungus among us.
And if the log was carved into a crotch-shape,
it would still work?
Not on your life!
Okay, got it.
That's a damn shame.
And here I thought we had the perfect storm of skill
and target audience to flood the Forestry department
with easy women.
Huh?
Oh, yeah. Of course.
If ever there was a product designed for fujoshi girls,
this would've been it. That lot loves their fantasy.
Fujoshi.
Genuine fujoshi.
Yeah!
Think of all the lonely ladies out there
who dream of you manly forestry types!
What you do is pure sex to them:
you hunks are like the Texas Rangers or something!
Right, Kousaku?
Huh? Oh, yeah! Absolutely!
Like I said, it's a damn shame.
Had we been able to make this work, there's no telling
how many free-wheeling gals
would've been falling over themselves to join Class F.
All those hotties desperate for
attention from big, strong men.
You know, maybe I was jumping the gun.
I should hear you out.
So here's the name.
Ugh. Brace for it, we're going with "Yeah.
Pick That Mushroom.
There You Go."
You're looking at hundreds of
years of mushroom cultivation
at its finest.
I give you the standard shiitake mushroom
with its dark, meaty cap!
The shimeji, with its cluster
of fleshy forking tendrils.
Hungry, anybody?
Eight inches of thick, magisterial heft.
The king trumpet!
The maitake, whose dark frills
give off an intoxicating scent.
Smell that musk!
The nameko, with it viscous
coat and suggestive skin-tone.
Careful ladies!
The lovely mukitake. Like a gymnast's six pack.
And the oyster, fungal art splayed like a mosaic.
This is the stuff!
Call now and we'll include with your order
the visually alluring fertilizer mix.
Our very special ANaL BB Yogurt Blend!
Now, for obvious reasons, we can't sell this stuff
through the usual networks. Not to worry, though:
we'll be moving units through
Bio's very own fujoshi pipeline!
Packaging will be plain.
The label will say "Folk Crafts."
Right.
Needless to say,
if anyone catches us selling these things,
we're toast. So let's keep everything on the DL.
We took advantage of our freedom, all right.
The world didn't know what hit it when we were done.
And we were done pretty quick.
Just as we were starting out.
We got busted.
Oh boy. Suspension.
My, Miss Kinoshita,
that yukata looks fabulous on you!
Think so?
Why yes!
They were made for flat-chested girls!
Just think. Caught 'cause one of the top
clients was a classmate's grandmother.
Yeah, well. Guess we had it coming.
Hey, look on the bright side.
It's like three days' vacation.
You got off a lot easier than your ring leader.
She had it much worse, appropriately.
Repeat offenders like her get three weeks' suspension.
And all of Class F got a formal
reprimand which, believe me,
you wouldn't have wanted.
So... what happened to them?
The forestry teacher, Mr. Tachikawa, beat their ass.
Yeesh.
Their summer break's going to suck, too.
They'll spend most of it on Mount Onake.
Oh snap. Mount Onake. No thanks.
I'm with you on that.
Hm?
Oh. Hey.
Got a new business idea brewing.
For when I get back.
What do you say? You interested?
Huh?
I've got everything lined up.
I just need your... front-man skills.
Didn't think so. Oh well.
One more thing.
Tell me. Did you have fun?
It's a simple yes or no.
Hmph. Yeah.
Then my work here is done.
Let's see how far we can take this mascot trend.
Ooh! How about a talking prolapsed anus?
Some people refuse to learn, huh?
Oh! Look at the bamboo!
Let's write wishes for the Star Festival!
Uhh... What should I wish for?
Ah, there we go!
This is cool.
Too many, you think?
Seems like kind of a lot, yeah.
I mean, it's good to want things, but...
You are not hanging these up!
Oh! I almost forgot!
I want you to tie me up!
Ugh. Who hired you?
I'm going to have a look at
what everyone else wished for.
I like Star Festivals.
We all wish for different things,
but the wishing brings us together.
The deal is, none of us gets
to be happy unless we all are.
Seems like a good thing to me.
No, really. Makes us a family.
Sob Salad.