- Alastor: SHORTLY AFTER THE
SECOND SEMESTER OF SCHOOL BEGAN,
YUJI BEGAN TO FEEL
AN EERIE SENSE OF DEJA VU.
THE REPETITION OF EVENTS
WAS REVEALED TO BE A DREAM
CREATED BY
A WEAK CRIMSON DENIZEN.
ONCE YUJI REALIZED
THE TRUTH,
SHANA MADE SHORT WORK
OF HER.
BUT THAT WAS NOT
THE END OF THE STORY.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( birds chirping )
- THERE, THAT'LL DO NICELY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- SORRY TO JUST DROP IN.
THANKS FOR THE HELP.
- I'M HAPPY TO HELP YOU LEARN
HOW TO MAKE A BOXED LUNCH,
SO PLEASE DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, DEAR.
THOUGH I MUST CONFESS
I'M CURIOUS--
WHY THE SUDDEN DESIRE
TO COOK?
- HERE, SAKAI.
I MADE THIS BOXED LUNCH FOR YOU.
- DELICIOUS.
YOU'RE A REALLY
FANTASTIC COOK.
- I JUST-- I DIDN'T LIKE IT.
- HUH?
- YUJI REALLY ENJOYED
THAT LUNCH SHE MADE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT IT BOTHERED ME
THAT HE LIKED IT SO MUCH.
- I SEE.
NOW WHY DON'T YOU GET
THE EGGS FROM THE FRIDGE?
- OKAY.
- JUST ONE MORE THING...
( chuckles )
- I AM INDEED SORRY TO BOTHER
YOU WITH SOMETHING AS SIMPLE
AS LEARNING HOW TO PREPARE
A BOXED LUNCH, MRS. SAKAI.
- THAT'S ENOUGH FROM YOU!
GET OUT OF HERE ALREADY!
WHY DON'T YOU GO TAKE CARE
OF YUJI'S TRAINING?
- BUT SHOULDN'T I BE
THE ONE TO--?
- JUST GO!
- I CERTAINLY DON'T MIND
TEACHING YOU, SHANA.
I'M HAPPY TO HELP.
BUT MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE
ASKED WILHELMINA FIRST.
I'M SURE SHE'D HAVE BEEN
PLEASED TO LEND A HAND.
- YEAH, BUT SHE
CAN'T COOK,
SO IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
POINTLESS TO ASK.
- I'LL BET THAT'S NOT
COMPLETELY TRUE.
EVERYBODY HAS A RECIPE OR TWO
UP THEIR SLEEVE.
I'M SURE
SHE DOES TOO.
- SHE CAN ONLY COOK THINGS
THAT GO IN THE MICROWAVE
OR THAT YOU POUR
BOILING WATER INTO
OR RAW STUFF.
BUT I WANT TO KNOW
HOW TO MAKE A MORE
SOPHISTICATED LUNCH THAN THAT.
- MM-HMM.
- I PUT THE EGGS IN HERE?
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
( sighs )
- ( exclaiming )
CAN'T YOU GIVE ME A BREAK?
- YOU'D BE A BETTER FIGHTER
IF YOU'D DODGE ATTACKS
BEFORE OPENING YOUR MOUTH.
YOU NEED TO FEEL
THE POWER OF EXISTENCE FLOWING.
- THAT'S EASY
FOR YOU TO SAY.
- ( Wilhelmina's voice )
SHE IS A PURE FLAME HAZE.
WHY DOES SHE FEEL
THE NEED TO WASTE TIME
LEARNING TO PREPARE
A BOXED LUNCH?
ON TOP OF WHICH,
SHE SELECTED
SOMEONE ELSE
AS HER INSTRUCTOR.
- Yuji: I GIVE.
- HER, NOT ME.
- ( screams )
- SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING,
SURELY YOU'VE NOT FORGOTTEN
THIS IS A TRAINING EXERCISE?
- Tiamat: GO EASIER ON HIM.
- Alastor: ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT, YUJI?
I KNOW
THAT WAS ROUGH.
AS FOR YOU,
SPECIALIST,
EVEN IF THIS IS A MYSTES,
YOU WENT TOO FAR.
TAKE CARE
IN THE FUTURE.
- I HAD SOMETHING
ON MY MIND.
WHAT WAS THAT POWER
IN HIM?
- YOU MUST HAVE BEEN DISTRACTED
IF YOU'VE ONLY NOW NOTICED
HIS INCREASING STRENGTH
IN BATTLE.
YUJI CARRIES FAR MORE
POWER OF EXISTENCE NOW.
IT IS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE HE LEARNS TO CONTROL IT.
- Tiamat: PALACE OF THE STARS.
- INDEED.
- Alastor: BY SYNCHRONIZING
WITH SUPREME THRONE HECATE,
IT SEEMS
THIS MYSTES BECAME
A PART OF THE FOUNTAIN
OF EXISTENCE.
HECATE'S EXISTENCE
IS ETERNAL.
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
SPILLED A GREAT AMOUNT
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE
INTO HER.
HOWEVER, THE BOY SEEMS TO HAVE
REGENERATED THAT LOST POWER.
IT'S ALMOST AS THOUGH
HE SUDDENLY HAS
AN ENDLESS SUPPLY
OF IT.
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
WILL BE CONTINUOUSLY REFILLED
AND ITS POWER AUGMENTED
BY THE FOUNTAIN.
- Tiamat: WHO WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT...
- Wilhelmina: THAT THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD HAD SUCH A POWER.
- Alastor: HMM, NOT I,
WHICH IS PRECISELY WHY
I'M HESITANT TO LEAVE
THIS CITY PRECIPITOUSLY.
- Bel-Peol: HOW LOW
HAVE WE FALLEN
THAT THE BAL MASQUE MUST LIVE
IN SUCH A PLACE AS THIS?
I KNOW THE PROFESSOR
IS LOOKING FORWARD TO IT,
BUT I'M AFRAID REPAIRING
THE PALACE OF THE STARS
IS GOING TO TAKE
QUITE SOME TIME.
STILL, THERE ARE PLENTY
OF OTHER THINGS
WE CAN TAKE CARE OF UNTIL THEN,
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- INDEED.
I'LL TAKE THAT AS MY CUE
TO GET BACK TO WORK.
- IT'LL BE SO LONELY
WITHOUT YOU.
- ( chuckles )
I'M SURE YOU'LL MANAGE.
I CAN TRUST YOU NOT TO DO
ANYTHING IMPOLITE
TO MY HECATE
WHILE I'M GONE?
- JUST WHAT ARE YOU IMPLYING?
- YOU HEARD WHAT I SAID.
LIKE THE BLUE INSIGNIA,
FOR INSTANCE.
- COME NOW,
I THOUGHT
WE WERE ALL WORKING
TOWARD A COMMON GOAL.
I'M SURE HECATE UNDERSTANDS
MY ACTIONS.
- A COMMON GOAL?
YOU COULD
CALL IT THAT.
I JUST DO MY JOB
AND DON'T ASK QUESTIONS.
- ( inhales sharply ) MM.
MY TRAINING WAS
WAY TOUGH TODAY.
I MEANT TO ASK YOU,
HOW COME I'M TRAINING
WITH WILHELMINA
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- BECAUSE YOU CAN DEVELOP
BAD HABITS
TRAINING WITH THE SAME PERSON
ALL THE TIME, THAT'S WHY.
- Alastor: ALSO,
THERE'S THE FACT
THAT YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE
HAS INCREASED EXPONENTIALLY.
- OH, YEAH,
THAT TOO.
YOU'RE ABOUT AS POWERFUL
AS A CRIMSON LORD THESE DAYS.
- I CAN'T SAY
I'VE NOTICED A CHANGE.
FOR SOME REASON IT'S HARD FOR ME
TO GET A FEEL FOR IT MYSELF.
- Alastor: THAT'S WHY WE MUST
CONTINUE YOUR TRAINING.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN TO CONTROL THE
POWER THAT IS NOW INSIDE YOU.
THANKFULLY,
YOU'VE ALREADY MASTERED
THE ART OF CASTING
A SEAL.
- YEAH.
- I GUESS SO.
- YOU'RE BECOMING
STRONGER, YUJI.
- IKE, YOU WANT TO GO
GRAB SOME LUNCH?
- WELL, I WOULD,
BUT YOU'VE ALREADY GOT LUNCH.
- HUH?
- HERE YOU GO, SAKAI.
I DECIDED TO MAKE A CLUB
SANDWICH FOR YOU TODAY.
- WOW, SOUNDS GREAT.
I BET THERE'S NOT A SINGLE
RECIPE YOU CAN'T MAKE.
- NO, THERE'S PROBABLY LOTS.
- I BROUGHT MY LUNCH TODAY,
SO WHY DON'T ALL OF US
EAT TOGETHER?
- Kazumi: I'LL GO GRAB US
SOME DRINKS.
- DUDE, DON'T MAKE HER
FEEL BAD.
- OH, YEAH.
- WELL, HERE WE GO.
- THANK YOU.
LOOKS GREAT.
- YUJI!
HERE.
- WHAT'S THIS?
- IT'S FOR YOU.
- YOU MADE IT?
THANKS, SHANA.
THAT WAS SWEET.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WERE DOING
THIS MORNING-- MAKING ME LUNCH?
- IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I'VE GOT MORE THAN I CAN EAT,
SO I THOUGHT I'D SHARE.
MAYBE I'LL DO IT AGAIN SOMETIME.
- WELL, THANK YOU.
LOOKS DELICIOUS.
- ( Yuji's voice ) THIS FOOD IS
GOOD, BUT THERE'S SO MUCH OF IT.
AND I'M NOT EVEN
ALL THAT HUNGRY THIS AFTERNOON.
CAN'T EAT MORE OF ONE
THAN THE OTHER.
( moaning )
( Yugi's voice )
IT HURTS.
- ( thud )
- SOMETHING WRONG?
SAKAI?
- YUJI!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( bells jingling )
- Shana: YUJI.
- IT WAS SWEET OF HIM
TO EAT EVERYTHING WE MADE,
BUT I THINK IT WAS TOO MUCH.
I HOPE
HE'LL BE OKAY.
- HERE'S A THOUGHT:
HOW ABOUT YOU STOP
BRINGING HIM LUNCHES EVERY DAY
SO HE DOESN'T END UP LIKE THIS?
DON'T YOU GET IT?
YUJI AND I
COULD BE FACED WITH A SERIOUS
FIGHT AT ANY GIVEN MOMENT.
AND HE'S NOT GONNA BE ANY HELP
IN THIS CONDITION.
- SORRY.
I UNDERSTAND.
I WON'T MAKE AS MUCH
ANYMORE.
- THE LUNCH I MAKE HIM
WILL BE FINE.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE SITUATION.
YUJI IS NOT A REGULAR
MYSTES ANYMORE,
SO STOP INTERFERING!
- THAT'S NOT FAIR.
I CARE AS MUCH AS YOU DO.
SEE, I MAY NOT
FULLY GET
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HIM
LIKE YOU,
BUT I DO KNOW
THAT I LOVE HIM.
AND I AM GONNA KEEP SHOWING HIM
THAT LOVE BY MAKING HIM LUNCHES.
YOU CAN'T STOP ME.
- WANNA BET?
- THERE'S MORE TO HIS LIFE
THAN FIGHTING ALONGSIDE YOU.
- I KNEW YOU WOULDN'T
UNDERSTAND.
IT'S NOT HER FAULT.
AFTER ALL, YOSHIDA'S ONLY HUMAN.
THERE'S NO WAY
SHE COULD COMPREHEND.
- ( bells jingle )
- IT'S A SEAL!
YUJI, WAKE UP!  YUJI!
- SHANA, LET HIM BE.
HE NEEDS HIS REST.
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THAT.
COME ON, GET UP.
THERE'S A DENIZEN HERE.
- WE NEED TO MOVE OUT.
- YEAH, OKAY.
- NO, WAIT.
SAKAI, I WANTED TO SAY--
NEVER MIND.
PLEASE BE SAFE OUT THERE.
- Yugi: THE MISAGO FESTIVAL.
- WE'RE IN THE SEAL,
BUT I DON'T FEEL A PRESENCE.
- WAIT.
SHANA, THIS IS THE BONFIRE
FROM THE FESTIVAL.
- THERE ARE MORE IMPORTANT
THINGS FOR US
TO FOCUS ON
RIGHT NOW.
- BUT IT MAKES NO SENSE.
IT'S SEPTEMBER.
THE MISAGO FESTIVAL
IS HELD IN AUGUST.
- WHICH MEANS...
HA!
IS IT JUST ME OR HAS SOMETHING
SIMILAR TO THIS HAPPENED BEFORE?
- ( bells jingle )
- Shana: WAKE UP!
DID YOU HEAR ME?
- WAIT A SEC.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
THE PAST
IS REPEATING AGAIN.
- ( bells jingle )
- Mare: A TRANSIENT,
AND YET ETERNAL AFFAIR.
- HOW COULD I FORGET
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
WAIT, SHANA.
IT'S A DREAM!
WE'RE INSIDE A DREAM AGAIN!
- WHAT?
- DON'T YOU SEE?
- SEE WHAT?  WHAT'S GOING ON?
- IT'S LIKE YESTERDAY.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
THAT DENIZEN MADE ME FALL INTO A
DREAM IN THE MIDDLE OF A BATTLE.
I HAD FORGOTTEN ABOUT IT UNTIL
NOW, BUT IT'S HAPPENING AGAIN.
THE PAST IS REPEATING ITSELF
ENDLESSLY.
- WHAT?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- WAIT.
- ( grunts )
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, HUH?
- ( chuckles ) GOOD.
I WAS JUST MAKING SURE
YOU'RE REAL.
- OKAY, YOU'RE SAYING THIS IS
ALL HAPPENING INSIDE OF A DREAM?
I NEVER WOULD HAVE EXPECTED
THAT CRIMSON DENIZEN
TO HAVE SUCH A SKILL.
- YEAH, I THOUGHT WE BEAT HER,
BUT I GUESS
I WAS WRONG.
- SHE'S STILL...
- ALIVE.
- IT IS WEIRD THOUGH.
LAST TIME I WOKE UP
WHEN I REALIZED
I WAS HAVING A DREAM.
AND NOW WE BOTH KNOW
WHAT IT IS,
SO WHY CAN'T WE WAKE UP?
THIS DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
- I GUESS WE'RE JUST
GONNA HAVE TO ASK HER.
- ( bells jingle )
- WHAT NOW?
- SOMETHING'S DEFINITELY UP.
IF THIS IS REALLY A DREAM,
THEN ONLY THINGS
WE'VE EXPERIENCED IN THE PAST
CAN HAPPEN
WHILE WE'RE HERE.
AM I RIGHT?
- YEAH, SO?
- WELL, WE SAW THE SEAL
BACK IN THE NURSE'S OFFICE.
SO THAT MEANS WE WERE ALREADY
IN A DREAM EVEN AT THAT POINT.
THEREFORE, YOSHIDA SHOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN ABLE TO SAY ANYTHING
THAT YOU AND I
DIDN'T ALREADY KNOW ABOUT.
BUT SHE DID.
- NO, WAIT.
SAKAI, I WANTED TO SAY--
NEVER MIND.
PLEASE BE SAFE OUT THERE.
- I DON'T REMEMBER
HER SAYING THAT BEFORE.
DO YOU?
OKAY, THEN THAT TOTALLY
VALIDATES MY THEORY.
YOU SEE?
- YEAH, I DO.
THIS IS YOSHIDA'S DREAM TOO,
ISN'T IT?
- AND IF SHE REALIZES THAT,
THEN WE'LL BE ABLE TO ESCAPE.
- YOSHIDA!
- ( chuckles )
- THAT JOKER'S THE DENIZEN
WHO'S BEHIND THIS DREAM?
- I DON'T KNOW.  IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE THE GIRL FROM YESTERDAY.
- HOW RUDE OF ME.
I HAVEN'T FORMALLY
INTRODUCED MYSELF.
MY NAME IS MARE,
THE KEEPER OF JESTFUL SLUMBER.
AND YOU'VE
FOUND ME OUT:
YOU'RE INSIDE GEMEINDE, MY MOST
POWERFUL UNRESTRICTED SPELL.
THIS WORLD WAS CREATED
USING YOUR MEMORIES.
- SO WHEN WE FOUGHT YOU
YESTERDAY,
WHAT WE KILLED WASN'T ACTUALLY
PART OF THE CORE OF YOUR BEING.
- NO, YOU ONLY KILLED
A MYSTES.
- ( bells jingle )
- A RATHER USEFUL ONE
THAT HAD THIS TREASURE TOOL
CALLED PAPAGENA.
I WAS SIMPLY INHABITING
ITS BODY.
- YOU'RE AWFULLY SMALL
FOR A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
NO WONDER I COULDN'T SENSE
YOUR PRESENCE.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT
WITH US?
- I'M STILL
FIGURING THAT OUT MYSELF.
( laughs )
- DO YOU WANT TO PLAY
WITH ME, LITTLE GIRL?
- YUJI, WHILE I'M
DEALING WITH HER,
I NEED YOU TO TRY AND FIND
A WAY TO WAKE UP YOSHIDA.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
WE'LL BE ABLE TO ESCAPE.
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
- ( Mare laughing )
INSIDE GEMEINDE,
EVERYTHING GOES AS I WANT IT TO.
TOO BAD FOR YOU.
YOUR FRIEND IS NEVER
GOING TO WAKE UP.
AND NEITHER WILL
THE TWO OF YOU.
- ( laughs )
I TRIED TO WARN YOU.
EVERYTHING GOES MY WAY
IN THIS WORLD.
- SHANA!
- ANOTHER THING YOU SHOULD KNOW:
YOU CAN DIE
IN YOUR DREAMS.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
GO AND WAKE UP YOSHIDA.
- NOT WISE--
TURNING YOUR BACK ON ME.
- ( Yuji's voice ) DREAM OR NOT,
THIS IS CRAZY.
HOW IS THAT THING NOT HURT
BY SHANA'S ATTACKS?
IT'S LIKE
IT'S NOT EVEN REAL.
- ( Shana's voice ) SO WHEN
WE FOUGHT YOU YESTERDAY,
WHAT WE KILLED WASN'T ACTUALLY
PART OF THE CORE OF YOUR BEING.
- IS IT POSSIBLE
THIS ISN'T THE CORE EITHER?
SO MAYBE...
- SEEMS YOU'RE NOT AS STUPID
AS YOU LOOK.
- SHANA,
SHE'S INSIDE OF ME!
MARE IS INSIDE
MY BODY!
- WHILE YOU TWO ARE BUSY
GIVING YOURSELVES HEART ATTACKS,
I'M GETTING EVEN CLOSER
TO THE TREASURE I SEEK.
AND YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE BEST PART?
YOU CAN'T TOUCH ME.
- NO.
- Mare: BECAUSE I'M
INSIDE THIS MYSTES.
- YUJI!
- NO WAY.
- ( Mare screams )
- THIS POWER--
IS IT A KEEPER?
- A KEEPER?
- IT'S A TREASURE TOOL
THAT BAL MASQUE
HAS BEEN AFTER.
IF I WERE
TO OBTAIN IT,
EVERYBODY WOULD
KNOW MY NAME
AND THEY WOULD
SEEK ME OUT.
ALL THAT'S LEFT
FOR ME
IS TO KILL THE MYSTES
WHO POSSESSES IT.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- IF I DIE,
THE DREAM WORLD I'VE CREATED
WILL COLLAPSE AROUND YOU.
WITHOUT THE GIRL,
YOU WILL NEVER WAKE.
YOU WILL NEVER BE ABLE
TO ESCAPE THE DREAM.
SO IN THE END,
I STILL WIN.
- Shana: DAMN IT.
- WAKE UP, YOSHIDA.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WAKE UP NOW.
YOSHIDA!
- ( mumbles )
SAKAI, IT'S YOU.
- HEY, WELCOME BACK.
- I HAD A DREAM.
- SHE'S AWAKENED?
IMPOSSIBLE.
( screams )
- ( clock chiming )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- THANK YOU.
YOU WERE GREAT.
WE'RE ALL STILL HERE
BECAUSE OF YOU, YOSHIDA.
YOU KNEW
IT WAS A DREAM.
I'M AMAZED.
- AMAZED?
DON'T BE.
SOMEHOW I KNEW YOU'D BE THERE
TO PULL ME OUT OF THE DARK.
WHATEVER I DID, IT WAS ONLY
SO I COULD SEE YOU AGAIN.
- YOU SAVED US.
- OH, NO.  SAKAI,
ARE YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
HE MUST BE EXHAUSTED.
- ( Shana's voice )
CAN'T LET HER GET TO ME.
WE'LL HAVE A MAJOR PROBLEM
IF THIS HAPPENS AGAIN,
SO BE CAREFUL WHAT YOU PACK
IN HIS LUNCH, OKAY?
UNLESS YOU WANT HIM
TO GET SICK.
- WOULD IT HELP IF I CUT
THE PORTION IN HALF?
- Alastor: A KEEPER?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- MM-HMM, WHEN THE DENIZEN
GOT INSIDE OF YUJI,
SHE NOTICED IT RIGHT AWAY.
IT SEEMS A STRONG KEEPER
HAS BEEN PUT
ON THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- Alastor: I NEVER
WOULD HAVE THOUGHT.
- A KEEPER.
INTERESTING.
- Sato: COME ON, MARGERY,
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'RE OVERDOING IT A BIT?
- FOR REAL.
WE CAN'T GO TO SCHOOL WHEN
YOU'RE HUNG OVER LIKE THIS.
- WHAT?  WAIT.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU BOYS
WERE INTO GOING TO SCHOOL.
- WELL, NOT REALLY.
- Marcosias: LISTEN TO THE KIDS.
THEY'VE GOT A POINT.
YOU'RE DRINKING
IS OUT OF LINE.
SHOW SOME SELF-CONTROL,
MY BELOVED MARGERY DAW.
- CAN'T HELP IT.
I NEED SOMETHING
TO CALM MY NERVES.
- ( ice clinks )
- Man: I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE
OUR NEW TRANSFER STUDENT.
THIS IS FUMINA KONOE.
IT MAY TAKE HER A WHILE
TO GET USED TO THINGS HERE,
SO I WANT YOU ALL
TO HELP HER OUT AS BEST YOU CAN.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- SHE MAY NEED SOMEONE...
- IS THIS ANOTHER DREAM?
- ...GET HER CAUGHT UP
ON OUR SCHOOLWORK
SO FAR.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( Yugi's voice )
OUT OF NOWHERE,
A GIRL WHO LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE
THE SUPREME THRONE HECATE
HAS TRANSFERRED
INTO OUR CLASS.
HOW CAN WE BE SURE
SHE'S REALLY HUMAN?
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT.
SHANA'S SUSPICIONS GROW,
UNTIL SHE FINALLY
POINTS HER SWORD AT KONOE
WHILE THE NEW GIRL
IS FROZEN IN A SEAL.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"THE SUSPICIOUS
TRANSFER STUDENT."