- Alastor: MARE, THE KEEPER
OF JESTFUL SLUMBER,
CAME IN SEARCH OF
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
THE FIGHT PUT EVERYONE
IN JEOPARDY,
BUT THE AFFECTION YOSHIDA HAS
FOR YUJI SAVED THEM ALL.
AS THE BATTLE
DREW TO A CLOSE,
THE EXISTENCE OF A KEEPER
WAS REVEALED.
LATER, A TRANSFER STUDENT
STRONGLY RESEMBLING
SUPREME THRONE HECATE
APPEARED AT YUJI'S SCHOOL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( students chattering )
- Man: THIS IS
FUMINA KONOE.
IT MAY TAKE HER A WHILE
TO GET USED TO THINGS HERE,
SO I WANT YOU ALL
TO HELP HER OUT AS BEST YOU CAN.
- THE SUPREME THRONE
HECATE?
- CAST A SEAL!
- Kazumi: SAKAI, SHANA.
- YOU'RE AWAKE.
BUT HOW?
- I ALWAYS MAKE SURE
TO CARRY THIS.
KHAMSIN GAVE IT TO ME.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WE'RE IN A SEAL.
- ANY THOUGHTS, ALASTOR?
- Alastor: HMM.
- SHE SEEMS FROZEN.
IF SHE CAN'T MOVE WITHIN THE
SEAL, THEN SHE'S HUMAN, RIGHT?
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?  WHY ARE
YOU SO SUSPICIOUS OF HER?
I MEAN, WHAT DID SHE
EVER DO TO YOU?
- WELL, NOTHING.
IT'S JUST SHE LOOKS LIKE
A MEMBER OF BAL MASQUE
WE'VE FACED OFF AGAINST BEFORE.
- HE MEANS
THE SUPREME THRONE HECATE.
SHE'S THE ONE
WHO USED YUJI
TO TRY AND CREATE A FOUNTAIN
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- I REMEMBER NOW.
DO YOU THINK SHE'S COME
BACK HERE LOOKING FOR SAKAI?
- Yuji: NO,
IT CAN'T BE HER.
IF IT WAS, THE SEAL
WOULDN'T HAVE STOPPED HER.
SHE'D STILL BE MOVING.
- Alastor: HMM,
EVEN SO...
- Shana: SHE LOOKS
JUST LIKE HER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
ALASTOR?
IS IT POSSIBLE
FOR A CRIMSON DENIZEN
TO IMITATE A HUMAN
THIS WELL?
- Alastor: IT'S NOTHING
I'VE EVER SEEN DONE BEFORE.
HOWEVER, THAT CERTAINLY DOESN'T
MEAN THAT IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- I SEE.
- SHANA, I KNOW
THEY LOOK ALIKE,
BUT I DON'T SENSE THE SAME THING
I DID WITH HECATE.
I HONESTLY DON'T THINK
IT'S HER.
- I WANT TO AGREE.
STILL...
I JUST DON'T BUY IT.  A GIRL
WHO LOOKS IDENTICAL TO HECATE
HAPPENS TO SHOW UP
IN THE SAME CITY AS YOU
AND AT THE SAME SCHOOL,
NO LESS?
- YEAH, IT'S WEIRD.
BUT WHAT CAN WE DO?
- Alastor: WE CANNOT MAINTAIN
THIS SEAL FOREVER, SHANA.
FOR NOW, WE'LL SIMPLY
HAVE TO STAY CAUTIOUS
AND KEEP A CLOSE EYE
ON HER.
- MISS HIRAI,
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, EVERYTHING'S FINE.
- ALL RIGHT.
AS I WAS SAYING,
KONOE HAS LIVED ABROAD
SINCE SHE WAS A CHILD.
SHE ONLY RECENTLY RETURNED
TO THIS COUNTRY
AND THEREFORE MIGHT REQUIRE
SOME ASSISTANCE.
- ( students chattering )
- I'M SURE
YOU CAN ALL IMAGINE
THE CULTURE SHOCK
SHE'S GOING THROUGH RIGHT NOW.
LET'S MAKE HER FEEL
WELCOME, OKAY?
- Students: YES, SIR.
- KONOE, NOW THAT WE'VE
INTRODUCED YOU TO THE CLASS,
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
THE EMPTY SEAT
TOWARD THE BACK
OF THE ROOM?
NO, THAT ONE'S TAKEN.
YOU CAN HAVE THE ONE
THAT'S A LITTLE FURTHER BACK.
- I WOULD LIKE TO SIT HERE.
- THIS IS MY DESK.
- BUT I WOULD LIKE
TO SIT THERE.
- WHAT?  NO.
TEACHER.
- WELL, IT IS
HER FIRST DAY.
OKAY, SUGANO, GO AHEAD
AND SWITCH SEATS WITH HER.
- Sugano: HUH?
- Shana:
THAT CAN'T BE A COINCIDENCE.
- Teacher: NOW LET'S
GET STARTED.
WHERE DID WE
LEAVE OFF?
UH, KONOE, DO YOU NOT HAVE
THE TEXTBOOKS FOR THIS COURSE?
- I HAVE THEM.
THEY'RE IN MY BAG.
- MM, THEN MAYBE
YOU COULD TAKE THEM OUT?
- YOU WANT ME
TO TAKE THEM OUT MYSELF?
- OF COURSE.
YOU DON'T REALLY EXPECT
SOMEONE ELSE TO DO THAT
FOR YOU, DO YOU?
- NO, I CAN DO IT.
- HERE, I'LL HELP YOU.
- Teacher: THANKS, SAKAI.
WILL YOU KEEP AN EYE ON HER?
- YES, SIR.
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS.
- NO PROB.
THAT'S STRANGE.
WHAT'S THIS?
OH, MY BUTLER GAVE ME THAT
TO COVER THE TOP OF MY DESK.
- SHE'S AN ODD DUCK.
THIS SHOULD BE FUN.
- HEY, SATO, WAKE UP.
SCHOOL'S ALREADY STARTED.
WE ARE SO LATE.
WE'RE GONNA BE DEAD MEAT.
- JUST FIVE MORE
MINUTES.
- ( laughs ) YOU POOR KIDS
DO KNOW YOU DON'T HAVE TO TRY
AND KEEP UP WITH HER
EVERY NIGHT, DON'T YOU?
- I'M INCLINED
TO AGREE WITH YOU.
- ALL OF A SUDDEN I'M SENSING
A SNEAKY PRESENCE
HERE IN MISAKI CITY.
- IS IT A DENIZEN?
- IT'S GOTTA BE.  BUT I DON'T
KNOW WHAT THEY'RE THINKING.
THERE ARE ALREADY THREE
FLAME HAZE STATIONED HERE.
IF THEY'RE SMART, THEN THEY'LL
LEAVE BEFORE WE CAN GET TO 'EM.
BUT IF NOT,
I GUESS I'LL HAVE TO--
( snoring )
- WHAT A LOVELY CITY.
SHOULD BE A FLAME HAZE
HERE SOMEWHERE,
HOPEFULLY ONE THAT CAN
KEEP ME ENTERTAINED.
- ( clock chiming )
- HEY, GUYS, THE P.E. SCHEDULE'S
BEEN SWITCHED UP,
SO THE BOYS ARE ON THE FIELD NOW
AND THE GIRLS ARE IN THE GYM.
- Students: OKAY.
- LISTEN, YUJI, I WANT YOU
TO KEEP YOUR GUARD UP.
WE CAN'T BE CERTAIN WHETHER
IT'S REALLY HER YET OR NOT.
- I KNOW.
- HEY, KONOE,
DID YOU BRING
GYM CLOTHES WITH YOU?
- YES.
- THINK YOU CAN CHANGE
INTO THEM YOURSELF
OR DO YOU NEED YOUR BUTLER
TO HELP YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I AM USED TO ASSISTANCE, BUT
I GUESS I COULD DO IT MYSELF.
- ( laughs )
WHAT, ARE YOU SOME KIND OF
FOREIGN PRINCESS OR SOMETHING?
I SWEAR, YOU ARE TOTALLY
CRACKING ME UP.
DON'T WORRY, I'LL HELP YOU OUT.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
KAZUMI.
- Yuji: DANG, SHE LOOKS
JUST LIKE HER.
- Shana: I WISH
THERE WAS SOME WAY
FOR US TO CONFIRM
OUR SUSPICIONS ABOUT HER.
- I STILL DON'T SENSE
THAT SHE'S A DENIZEN.
- YOU WOULDN'T.
- WE'VE GOT SOMETHING ELSE
TO DEAL WITH ANYWAY.
- OH, DO WE?
- THERE'S A DENIZEN SOMEWHERE
ON THE EDGE OF TOWN.
CAN YOU NOT SENSE
ITS PRESENCE?
- I THINK I'LL JUST
LET IT BE FOR NOW.
HECATE IS MUCH MORE
IMPORTANT.
BUT I AM IMPRESSED
THAT YOU NOTICED IT WAS THERE.
- SHE COMPLIMENTED ME.
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY IS SHE IGNORING
THE DENIZEN?
THAT CAN'T BE SAFE.
- OKAY, ARMS UP.
THERE WE GO.
TRY TO HOLD STILL, OKAY?
NO STRUGGLING.
GOOD.  ALL FINISHED.
- Fumina: I CAN'T BRING MYSELF
TO BELIEVE
THIS SWEET GIRL
IS ONE OF THEM.
I HOPE THEY'RE WRONG
ABOUT HER.
- ( students chattering )
- Kazumi: IF KONOE REALLY IS A
CRIMSON DENIZEN,
THEN THAT MEANS
SHE'S AFTER SAKAI.
- ( blows whistle )
- Girl: COME ON!
YOU CAN DO IT!
- I THOUGHT EVERYTHING WAS
FINALLY BACK TO NORMAL.
BUT NOW THE ONE I CARE ABOUT
MOST IS IN DANGER AGAIN.
NOTHING'S SIMPLE
ANYMORE.
I SHOULD HAVE
EXPECTED THAT.
- Ogata: LOOK OUT, KAZUMI!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I THINK SO.
- I DIDN'T MEAN
TO HURT YOU.
- I'M OKAY.
NO NEED TO CRY.
- ( whistle blows )
- ( students cheering )
- SO, KONOE...
- UH-HUH?
WHEN YOU WERE CHOOSING
YOUR SEAT THIS MORNING,
WELL I-- I NOTICED THAT
YOU WANTED TO SIT BY SAKAI.
WAS THERE ANY REASON?
- WHO'S SAKAI?
- YOU DON'T REMEMBER HIM?
HE'S THE BOY
WHO SITS NEXT TO YOU.
- OH, THAT'S HIS NAME?
- I'M SORRY.  I SHOULDN'T HAVE
EXPECTED YOU TO KNOW THAT.
IT'S JUST, WELL, I--
I-- I WONDERED IF YOU KNEW
SAKAI FROM SOMEWHERE,
YOU KNOW, LIKE YOU HAD MET HIM
OR RUN INTO HIM BEFORE,
AND WHETHER YOUR TRANSFER TO OUR
SCHOOL WAS JUST A COINCIDENCE
OR POSSIBLY A CHANCE
FOR YOU TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
UM, KONOE?
YOU AWAKE?
MAYBE THEY'RE JUST
OVERANALYZING THINGS.
- YOU HUNGRY?
IT'S LUNCHTIME.
I KNOW.  BUT I CAN'T START
EATING UNTIL IT GETS HERE.
- UH, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I'M WAITING FOR LUNCH.
- DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE WAITING
FOR SOMEBODY TO BRING IT TO YOU.
- HMM?
- YOU'RE HYSTERICAL.
NOBODY IS GONNA
WAIT ON YOU HERE.
WAIT ALL YOU WANT,
BUT LUNCH ISN'T COMING.
WE HAVE TO GO TO IT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ARE YOU COMING?
- UH, WELL, NO.
I ALREADY HAVE A LUNCH.
- I SEE.
- ( Ogata chuckles ) LOOKS LIKE
SOMEONE HAS A LITTLE CRUSH.
COME ON, KONOE.
( laughs )
- THAT GIRL'S RIDICULOUS.
HOW PAMPERED
CAN ONE PERSON BE?
- UH, SAKAI,
I KNOW SHANA'S SUSPICIOUS
BUT I DON'T THINK
KONOE'S ONE OF THEM.
- HMM, YEAH.
- I THINK IT'S ALL
JUST AN ACT.
- Ike: WHAT'RE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- OH.
- THERE YOU GUYS ARE.
WILL YOU EVER MAKE IT
TO CLASS ON TIME?
- CHILL OUT.
- THAT CHICK WE JUST SAW--
I DIDN'T RECOGNIZE HER.
IS SHE A NEW STUDENT?
- MM-HMM.
WAIT.
- ( Sato over speaker )
MARGERY, MARGERY,
PLEASE PICK UP.
- HEY, WAKE UP!
YOU GOT A CALL.
- NOT SO LOUD.
YEAH?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- ARE YOU SURE IT'S WISE TO RELY
ON THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES?
- WHY NOT?  SHE IS A SPECIALIST
IN UNRESTRICTED SPELLS.
- Alastor: HMM.
- I GUESS WE COULD USE ANOTHER
SET OF EYES ON THIS ONE.
AND THIS WOULD BE THE PERFECT
PLACE TO CAST A SPELL.
- ( laughs )
THERE YOU ARE,
MY PRETTIES.
I SMELL
EVERY ONE OF YOU.
- Ogata: THIS ONE'S NOT BAD,
BUT IF I WERE YOU,
I'D STAY AWAY FROM THAT ONE.
OOH, AND THAT ONE TOO.
WHERE'D SHE GO?
- ( chirping )
- THESE BIRDS ARE HERE
IN JAPAN TOO.
IS THIS YOUR HOME,
LITTLE BIRDIES?
- HUH, I'M NOT SURPRISED
THE MIDGET
IS SUSPICIOUS OF HER.
- Marcosias: THAT'S SOME CRAZY
STUFF!  SHE WASN'T KIDDING!
THEY'RE LIKE
IDENTICAL TWINS.
- JUST PHYSICALLY THOUGH.
I DON'T SENSE THE POWER IN HER.
WELL, WE SHOULD PROBABLY
CHECK HER OUT ANYWAY.
WHEN A MAN
HAS MARRIED A WIFE...
- Marcosias: HE FINDS OUT
WHETHER...
HER KNEES AND ELBOWS
ARE ONLY GLUED TOGETHER!
- HUH?  HUH?
DON'T GO.
- KONOE, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
THE FOOD WAS GOING QUICK,
SO I GRABBED YOU SOMETHING.
- THAT WAS NICE,
THANK YOU.
- Marcosias: HUH.
NO REACTION AT ALL.
- Margery: SHE DIDN'T EVEN
NOTICE THE UNRESTRICTED SPELL.
WE'VE DONE OUR PART.
NOW IT'S UP TO THE MIDGET.
- THAT WAS A SPELL.
NOW I GOTCHA.
( chuckles )
- Yuji: WELL, MARGERY TESTED HER
AND SHE PASSED,
SO THERE'S NO WAY
KONOE IS HECATE.
- MAYBE NOT, BUT I'M STILL
NOT GONNA LET MY GUARD DOWN.
I NEED MORE PROOF
BEFORE I CAN BE SURE OF THAT.
- I MIGHT BE
OUT OF LINE,
BUT SHOULD YOU LET THAT MUCH
OF YOUR POWER LEAK OUT
WHILE YOU'RE JUST
WALKING AROUND?
THAT DENIZEN IS STILL
AWFULLY CLOSE BY.
SHOULDN'T WE, I DON'T KNOW,
DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
- YUJI, I THINK
YOU SHOULD HEAD HOME.
- WHY?
- JUST DO IT!
- SHANA.
- Alastor: WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
WHY DID YOU CHOOSE
TO ABANDON THE MYSTES
LIKE THAT?
- 'CAUSE HE'LL ONLY
GET IN MY WAY.
- AH, DUE TO
THE BRUTALITY INVOLVED.
- HUH?
THIS MUST BE
WHERE YOU LIVE, HUH?
- THE PERFECT PLACE
TO TAKE THEM ON.
- Alastor: IT SEEMS THE DENIZEN
HAS NOTICED US.
IT'S COMING.
- HMM.
I'M GOING TO PERFORM A TEST
TO DETERMINE
WHETHER OR NOT YOU'RE
THE SUPREME THRONE HECATE.
- HECATE?
- CAST A SEAL!
- ( laughing )
I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR YOU,
PRECIOUS FLAME HAZE.
HA-HA!
GOOD.  YOU'RE GONNA
PUT UP A FIGHT.
YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN BEAT ME--
KASHA, ALSO KNOWN AS THE DEBRIS
OF THE DASHING CROOK?
- CAN'T SAY
I'VE HEARD THE NAME.
- HE DOESN'T SEEM
TO RECOGNIZE US EITHER.
HE MUST BE A NEWBORN.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT MY REPUTATION'S
GOTTA START SOMEWHERE.
HA!
( laughing )
SEE WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU TOUCH MY RINGS?
THEY'RE A POWERFUL TREASURE TOOL
CALLED CHORDE.
HOW THE HELL WERE YOU ABLE
TO HURT ME LIKE THAT?
- YOU'RE JUST
A NEWBORN,
EASILY BEATEN
BY SOMEONE OF MY STRENGTH.
- Alastor: SO WEAK
FOR SUCH BIG TALK.
YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN MORE
CAUTIOUS WITH YOUR WORDS.
- ( laughs )
THAT'LL TEACH YOU
TO UNDERESTIMATE ME.
AWW, BUT I FORGOT TO ASK THAT
LITTLE FLAME HAZE HER NAME.
HOW WILL I BRAG
ABOUT MY SUCCESS?
- YOU WANT TO KNOW
MY NAME?
I'M THE FLAMING-HAIRED,
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
AND MY NAME IS SHANA!
- FLAMING-HAIRED,
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
BUT THAT MEANS YOU'RE THE FLAME
OF THE HEAVEN'S--
- Alastor: WELL,
I GIVE YOU CREDIT
FOR RECOGNIZING
THE TITLE AT LEAST.
- I HAVE TO HEAL MY ARM.
I NEED POWER.
I NEED
POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- SHANA!
- IF THAT IS HECATE,
SHE WON'T LET THE DENIZEN
KILL HER.  WE'LL KNOW THE TRUTH.
- Yuji: THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE HOLDING BACK?
- POWER.
POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- SHANA YOU CAN'T
DO THIS TO HER.
KONOE'S A HUMAN BEING.
FIGHT HIM.
- KONOE!
- BLOOD.
- SHE IS HUMAN.
- Alastor: YES.
- Yuji: I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU WERE
BAITING THAT DENIZEN
JUST SO YOU COULD
TEST KONOE.
- I ASSUMED THAT KASHA WAS
AVOIDING THE CITY
BECAUSE HE COULDN'T
FIGURE OUT EXACTLY
WHERE THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
AND I WERE LOCATED.
BUT AS SOON AS THE CHANTER USED
AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL ON KONOE,
KASHA WAS FINALLY ABLE TO
SENSE US AND HE TOOK THE BAIT.
LUCKILY, IT ALL WENT
EXACTLY AS I HAD PLANNED.
- REALLY?  AND WHAT IF KONOE
HAD BEEN KILLED
BY THAT DENIZEN?
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE THEN?
- I SAVED HER, DIDN'T I?
SHUT IT.
- STILL...
- I HAD TO TAKE THE CHANCE.
NOW WE KNOW FOR SURE SHE'S
HUMAN, SO YOU CAN CONCENTRATE
ON YOUR TRAINING AGAIN.
WILHELMINA'S WAITING.
- UH...
- YOU ARE READY, AREN'T YOU?
- SURE.
- I HAVE TRIED
MY HARDEST, MISTRESS.
I HOPE I DID WELL.
- INDEED.
YOU DID VERY WELL.
PERFECTLY, IN FACT.
IT'S JUST
WHAT I WANTED,
FECOR.
- THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
I'M GLAD.
AT LEAST WE KNOW
KONOE'S NOT A DENIZEN.
- NOPE.  SHE JUST HAPPENS
TO LOOK LIKE ONE.
- THAT'S AWESOME.
WE CAN GO BACK TO NORMAL.
OH, HEY THERE, KONOE.
GOOD MORNING.
- GOOD MORNING
TO YOU AS WELL.
I'M GETTING READY
FOR CLASS.
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY
TAKING 'EM OUT ONE AT A TIME.
IT'S A LOT EASIER
THAT WAY.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
A FEATHER IN YOUR HAIR.
- A FEATHER?
YEAH.  SORRY, IT'S PRETTY
TANGLED IN THERE.
CAN YOU TILT YOUR HEAD
TOWARD ME?
OKAY, ALMOST GOT IT.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji:
SHANA SEEMS TO HAVE GIVEN UP
HER SUSPICIONS
REGARDING KONOE.
BUT EVERY TIME SHANA SEES HER
STANDING NEXT TO ME,
I CAN SENSE HER EMOTIONS
WELLING UP WITHIN HER.
THE SAME GOES
FOR YOSHIDA TOO.
I GUESS WE ALL
HAVE A HARD TIME
GETTING USED TO FEELINGS
WE'VE NEVER EXPERIENCED BEFORE.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"THE DISTRESSED GIRLS."