- Announcer: EVERYONE IS SHOCKED
TO LEARN YUJI'S FLAME IS SILVER.
DURING HER INVESTIGATION,
WILHELMINA LEARNED THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD'S CREATOR, HER OLD
FRIEND PHELES, IS STILL ALIVE.
THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL WAS ABRUPTLY
INTERRUPTED BY A HOWLING WIND.
SUDDENLY, YUJI FOUND
HIMSELF FACE TO FACE
WITH THE CAPRICE OF BEAUTY
HERSELF.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( screaming )
- YUJI!
- THAT COLOR.
- IT CAN'T BE.
- Marcosias: HOPE YOU'RE READY
FOR A THROWDOWN, LADIES!
- JOHAN, MY LOVE.
- ( gasps, heart beats )
- NO!
- YUJI. SHE'LL DESTROY HIM.
- IT'S PHELES.
- Tiamat: HIS FATE WAS SEALED.
- SHE FOUND HIM.
- HIS FATE WAS SEALED.
- WHAT DOES THIS DENIZEN
WANT WITH ME?
- I'VE BEEN SEARCHING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
- IT'S HER,
THE ONE WILHELMINA
WARNED ME ABOUT.
- I SHALL FREE YOU.
- NO, YOU CAN'T!
- ( screaming )
- ( laughing )
- Marcosias:
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
YES!
I FOUND YOU.
FINALLY, I WILL HAVE MY REVENGE.
- Marcosias: MARGERY!
- ( roars )
- PHELES.
- HIS FATE WAS SEALED.
- THE POOR BOY.
- BASTARD, I WILL KILL YOU!
- IF YOU DON'T CALM DOWN, I WILL
BE FORCED TO RESTRAIN YOU.
- ( roaring )
- ( snarls )
- WILHELMINA!
- LEAVE THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
TO THE SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING.
FOCUS ON PHELES.
- JOHAN.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG.
NOW COME TO ME.
- ( gasps )
- JOHAN, MY LOVE.
- NO!
- ( screaming )
- ( screams )
- GO!  GET OUT OF HERE!
- ( grunts )
- CAPRICE OF BEAUTY,
PLEASE LISTEN FOR A MOMENT.
- I CAN'T SENSE
HER PRESENCE ANYMORE.
- IT'S HER INVERNA SPELL.
IT GIVES HER THE ABILITY
TO OBSCURE HER PRESENCE.
YOU'LL HAVE TO KEEP
AN EYE OUT FOR HER.
- ( grunting )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, DUDE?
- THINK SO.
HEY, WHAT'S UP WITH THIS SEAL?
- SATO!
- IT'S MARGERY.
- STOP IT!
- WAKE UP.  WE GOTTA MOVE.
- OH, SATO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I'M NOT SURE,
BUT WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE.
COME ON.  TANAKA!
- NO WAY.
WHAT THE HELL'S GOTTEN INTO HER?
IF SHE KEEPS THIS UP, SHE'S
GONNA WRECK THE WHOLE SCHOOL.
- LET'S GO!
WE GOTTA FIND SOMEWHERE SAFE.
- ( roaring )
- YOU THINK SHE'S PISSED
'CAUSE OF THE SEAL?
- YEAH, LOOK.
- Kazumi: IT'S SILVER.
- THE CREEP MARGERY'S BEEN
SEARCHING FOR ALL THESE YEARS.
HE HAS A SILVER FLAME.
IT LOOKS LIKE
WILHELMINA'S TRYING TO HOLD
HER BACK FOR SOME REASON.
- Sato: WHY?
- NO CLUE.  WHAT'S UP?
- NOBODY COULD'VE CAST
THAT SEAL BUT HIM.
THE SILVER'S GOTTA BE HERE.
YOU THINK IT MIGHT BE THAT
DENIZEN WHO SHOWED UP OUT
OF NOWHERE
AND CAUSED ALL THIS MESS?
- NO, THAT'S THEIR
FLAME OVER THERE.
IT'S SOMEBODY ELSE, WHICH
MEANS IT'S SOMEONE WE KNOW.
IT MUST BE HIM.
WHO ELSE COULD IT BE?
- WHO DO YOU THINK IT IS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
DAMN IT.
I KNOW HE'S OUT THERE FIGHTING
WHILE I JUST SIT HERE.
- SHE'S GONNA HURT
ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
BE CAREFUL, MARGERY!
- GET BACK HERE.
- WATCH OUT!
- ( screaming )
- COME HERE, DUDE.
DON'T LET IT GET TO YOU.
IT'S OKAY.
THEY'LL RESTORE EVERYTHING
BEFORE THEY TAKE DOWN THE SEAL.
( wailing )
DAMN IT.  I'M USELESS.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
- SHE MUST BE LOSING POWER.
SHE'S SLOWING.
- ( snarls )
I WILL HAVE MY REVENGE!
- CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- WHAT?
YOU WERE HIDING HIM ALL ALONG?
- ENOUGH, MARGERY!
- STAY OUT OF THIS.
- PHELES.
- DON'T!  CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- SHE WON'T LISTEN.
- SHE MUST BE STOPPED.
- THEN LET'S DO IT.
( shouts )
GOOD.  SHE'S GETTING WEAKER.
- Margery Monster: DAMN IT!
- ( roars )
- ENOUGH, BOTH OF YOU.
NOW SIT DOWN AND SHUT UP.
- Tiamat:
EXCELLENT TEAMWORK.
- Shana:
DID YOU EXPECT ANYTHING LESS
FROM WILHELMINA AND ME?
- PLEASE, I'M BEGGING YOU.
LET US EXPLAIN THE SITUATION.
- Tiamat: A HUMBLE REQUEST.
- HEY, LISTEN TO 'EM,
WOULD YOU?
- HOW SHOULD WE
BREAK THE NEWS?
- Sato: I GOT IT.
SAKAI, HOW LONG WERE YOU
PLANNING TO HIDE
YOUR SILVER FLAME
FROM THE REST OF US?
CAT'S OUT OF THE BAG NOW.
- MARGERY, YOU ASSUMED SAKAI
WAS THE SILVER
JUST 'CAUSE OF HIS FLAME?
IF HE WAS, DON'T YOU THINK
HE WOULD'VE SHOWN
HIS TRUE COLORS BY NOW?
SAKAI MAY BE THE LINK WE NEED
TO FIND THE SILVER.
KILL HIM AND IT'S GONE.
- INDEED, THIS IS WHAT I PLANNED
TO TELL YOU
IN OUR MEETING
TOMORROW NIGHT.
- Tiamat: PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
- LISTEN TO US.
- SATO.
- JUST SHUT UP AND STAY BACK,
WOULD YOU?
- MARGERY.
HOW COULD YOU?
I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU WANT REVENGE
AGAINST THE SILVER.
I DO.
I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU WENT BERSERK,
BUT TODAY, WHAT--
WHAT YOU DID.
THAT EXPLOSION YOU CAUSED.
OGATA WAS RIGHT THERE.
OGATA WAS-- ( sobbing )
AND I WATCHED HER.
- YOU KNOW WHAT YOU DID.
YOU WERE AWARE.
YOU COULD HEAR EVERY WORD
WE SAID, COULDN'T YOU?
BUT IT DIDN'T MATTER.
THIS JUST PROVES YOU COULDN'T
CARE LESS ABOUT US.
ALL YOU CARE ABOUT IS SOME
100-YEAR-OLD VENDETTA.
DAMN YOU, MARGERY.
Marcosias: I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT THE KID'S RIGHT, MARGERY.
YOU'VE GOT TO THINK
BEFORE YOU ACT.
WHAT KIND OF EXAMPLE ARE YOU
SETTING FOR THESE TWO?
YOU KNOW THEY LOOK UP TO YOU.
ARE YOU SO HELL-BENT ON REVENGE
THAT YOU'D RISK
THE LIVES OF OTHERS?
DESTROYING ANYTHING
AND EVERYTHING
THAT GETS IN YOUR WAY?
TODAY I SAW A SIDE OF YOU
I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE,
AND I DIDN'T LIKE IT.
IF YOU LET HIM CONSUME YOU
LIKE THAT, HE'S ALREADY WON.
- MARGERY.
- LEAVE HIM ALONE.
- SO YOU'RE NOT A DENIZEN?
- NO, HE'S NOT.
- AND HE'S NOT THE SILVER.
- THERE'S CLEARLY A CONNECTION,
BUT WE'RE STILL INVESTIGATING.
- I SEE.
THEN WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
- I WISH I COULD TELL YOU.
I'D LIKE TO KNOW MYSELF.
- YEAH?
- YUJI!
- PHELES, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE DEAD.
- WILHELMINA.
- MAY I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
WHY DID YOU CALL THE MYSTES
BY THE NAME JOHAN?
I KNOW THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
WITHIN HIM
IS A MEMENTO
OF YOUR ETERNAL LOVER.
BUT YOU DO KNOW
JOHAN IS GONE.
- NO, HE IS STILL ALIVE.
- WHAT?
- I SEALED HIM INSIDE
THE TREASURE TOOL.
SABRAC.
THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE
HAD ATTACKED US.
HE WANTED TO TAKE
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- Wilhelmina: I SHOULD'VE
KNOWN HE WAS TO BLAME.
- Shana: WHO IS SABRAC?
- Whilhelmina: A POWERFUL
CRIMSON LORD INDEED.
HE IS WIDELY KNOWN
AS AN ASSASSIN.
- Pheles: JOHAN HAD
BEEN INJURED.
I PROTECTED HIM THE ONLY WAY
I KNEW HOW.
MY LOVE, WE WILL BE REUNITED.
I'VE BEEN SEARCHING
FOR HIM EVER SINCE.
AND NOW
I HAVE FINALLY FOUND HIM.
- I'M SORRY.
I ALWAYS ASSUMED THAT YOU
AND JOHAN HAD BEEN KILLED.
- PLEASE, FRIEND.
LET ME FREE MY BELOVED.
- PHELES, THIS MYSTES MAY BE
CARRYING A DANGEROUS PHENOMENON
KNOWN AS THE SILVER.
IT WOULD BE BEST TO POSTPONE
YOUR REUNION WITH JOHAN
UNTIL WE KNOW MORE.
- UNTIE ME.
- PHELES, I KNOW YOU
DO NOT TRUST HER.
BUT I AM INDEED BEGGING YOU,
MILADY.
PLEASE DO NOT KILL THE CAPRICE
OF BEAUTY JUST YET.
SHE DOES NOT CONSUME HUMAN POWER
OF EXISTENCE,
SO SHE IS NOT A THREAT
TO YOUR FRIENDS.
- Tiamat: PLEASE SPARE HER.
- WILHELMINA.
- I WOULD LIKE TO LEARN MORE
ABOUT THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
I SUPPOSE IT'LL BE SAFE
TO KEEP HER AROUND.
HER LACK OF POWER IS PROOF
THAT SHE DOESN'T PREY ON HUMANS.
- VERY ADMIRABLE OF YOU,
I MUST SAY.
ADMIRABLE INDEED, MILADY.
JOHAN.  THE OTHER HALF
OF THE ENGAGED LINK
IS INSIDE OF ME.
- AT TIMES LIKE THIS,
SAKAI FEELS SO DISTANT.
LIKE HE'S WORLDS AWAY.
- I COULD REALLY USE A DRINK.
- INDULGE ALL YOU WANT
WHEN WE GET HOME.
I WON'T PESTER YOU THIS ONCE.
- THANK YOU.
WHAT?
- I WOULD LIKE TO THANK YOU
FOR THE RESTRAINT
YOU SHOWED EARLIER.
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE THANKING ME.
I SHOULD BE APOLOGIZING
TO YOU.  SO WHAT'S UP?
- WE'RE GOING TO PERFORM
A RESTORATION
USING YUJI SAKAI'S
POWER OF EXISTENCE.
THE FLAMING-HAIRED BLAZING-EYED
HUNTER IS WARY
OF HAVING PHELES PRESENT
WHEN WE DO SO.
I WILL STAY WITH HER,
AND YUJI WILL SEND ME HIS POWER
THROUGH MY RIBBONS.
- SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF WORK
FOR YOU.
- ONE THING, BEFORE WE GO.
- MARGERY DAW,
CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
YOU ARE WELL KNOWN FOR YOUR
BRILLIANT SPELL CASTING.
WILL YOU HELP ME?
SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
I AM CONCERNED
ABOUT JOHAN'S SAFETY.
THE TREASURE TOOL SHOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO PRODUCE
A SILVER FLAME LIKE THAT.
- SO IT'S LIKE AN EGG.
AND THE ETERNAL LOVER
IS LOCKED AWAY INSIDE OF IT.
- I GUESS THAT MAKES THE MYSTES
THE EGGSHELL, HUH?
- IT COULD HAVE BEEN
SABRAC'S DOING
BEFORE IT WAS SEALED,
HE CAST SOME KIND
OF SPELL ON IT PERHAPS.
- I HATE TO LET YOU DOWN,
BUT DESPITE WHAT YOU THINK
I'M CAPABLE OF,
I'M NOT SURE I CAN BE
OF MUCH HELP TO YOU HERE.
- SAYS THE WOMAN
WHO'S BEEN KNOWN
TO IMPROVISE INCANTATIONS
AT THE DROP OF A HAT.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING!
( screams )
- AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU'D BE MUCH BETTER OFF
ASKING SOMEBODY LIKE THE SEEKER
OR THE CORPSE COLLECTOR
FOR THEIR HELP.
HE TOLD ME THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
- Lamies:
WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT,
THE SILVER WILL
APPEAR BEFORE YOU.
- IT LOOKS LIKE THAT
TIME HAS COME.
I NEED TO FOCUS ON THE PRESENT
INSTEAD OF WORRYING
ABOUT THE PAST.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE READY
FOR YOU.
- I'LL START RIGHT AWAY.
- SO YUJI AND THE MIDGET
ARE INSIDE THE SCHOOL?
- INDEED.  THE OTHERS ARE
WITH THEM AS WELL.
- KEISAKU AND EITA.
WELL, THERE'S ONLY
ONE THING TO DO.
LET ME TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
- I KNOW.  I WANT TO.
CALL IT A WHIM.
- Marcosias: YOU TRYING TO ATONE
FOR YOUR SINS?
- I'M THE ONE
WHO MADE THIS MESS.
I SHOULD BE THE ONE
TO CLEAN IT UP.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
- YOU'RE GOING TO PERFORM
THE RESTORATION, MARGERY?
YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
I'M JUST SURPRISED.
- ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA TAKE
THE RESTORATION BACK
TO BEFORE PHELES' ARRIVAL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE INJURED
IN THE CHAOS
AND I'D LIKE TO FIX THAT.
YOU JUST KEEP YOUR SEAL UP
AS LONG AS YOU CAN
AND I'LL TAKE CARE OF THE REST,
OKAY?
- RIGHT.  I'LL DO MY BEST.
- I'M SO SORRY, MATAKE.
I PROMISE I'LL MAKE IT UP
TO YOU SOMEHOW.
- Sorry, folks, we had some
technical difficulties
due to the wind.
Now let's get back to announcing
our grand prize winners!
- ( cheering )
- JEEZ, I THOUGHT THIS DAY
WOULD NEVER END
AND THERE'S STILL TOMORROW.
- HERE.
- THANKS.
- SORRY ABOUT--
YOU KNOW.
- ONE DAY I WILL CATCH UP
TO YOU.
SOMETIMES IT FEELS LIKE
YOU'RE SO FAR AWAY.
BUT I PROMISE ONE DAY
I'LL CATCH UP.
AND KNOWING WHAT'S GOING ON
IN YOUR LIFE MAKES ME FEEL
CLOSER TO YOU.
- YOSHIDA.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- HEY, TANAKA.  ARE YOU OKAY?
SATO ASKED ME TO COME
AND CHECK ON YOU.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- OGATA.
- TANAKA?
- OGATA, IT IS YOU.
YOU'RE OKAY.
OH, THANK GOD.
- GUESS WE'RE BOTH WINNERS, HUH?
- CONGRATULATIONS, SHANA.
- YEAH, THANK YOU.
AND THIRD PLACE ISN'T TOO SHABBY
EITHER, KAZUMI.  NICE JOB.
- ( mouthing )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: AS PHELES LOSES
STRENGTH, SHE TELLS THE STORY
OF HER ETERNAL LOVER, JOHAN,
AND THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
LITTLE DOES SHE KNOW,
THE TREASURE TOOL SHE CREATED
IS BEING MUTATED FROM WITHIN
BY A DANGEROUS FORCE.
WHILE THE OTHERS REMAIN
SKEPTICAL OF HER,
YOSHIDA INVITES PHELES
TO THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL.
NEXT TIME ON
"SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND"...
"ETERNAL LOVERS."