- Alastor: SHANA
SUSPECTS THAT TRANSFER STUDENT
FUMINA KONOE MAY ACTUALLY BE
THE SUPREME THRONE HECATE,
FORCING A RISKY CHOICE
WHEN A DENIZEN APPEARS.
WHILE IN MORTAL DANGER
IN THE SEAL,
FUMINA DOESN'T MOVE AN INCH,
THUS CLEARING HER OF SUSPICION.
HOWEVER, WATCHING FUMINA AND
YUJI SPEND TIME TOGETHER
HAS CAUSED PANGS OF JEALOUSY
DEEP WITHIN SHANA'S HEART.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( birds chirping )
- SO, SINCE YOU'RE STILL GETTING
ADJUSTED TO MISAKI CITY,
WE'LL COME BY AND PICK YOU UP
FOR SCHOOL IN THE MORNINGS.
LET US KNOW
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING
AND WE'LL DO WHATEVER WE CAN
TO HELP YOU OUT.
- OH, THANK YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN SO HELPFUL.
- Teacher: KONOE,
ARE YOU HAVING A HARD TIME
OVER THERE?
I GUESS I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO ASK SOMEONE
TO LOOK AFTER HER
FULL-TIME.
HMM.
AH.
- HUH?  ME?
ARE YOU SURE?
- YOU'RE THE MOST
RESPONSIBLE KID IN CLASS.
KONOE, WHY DON'T YOU GO
TAKE A SEAT NEXT TO IKE?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
GO AHEAD.
EH?
- WHY IS SHE SO ATTACHED
TO YOU, YUJI?
- GIVE HER A CHANCE,
WILL YOU?
I DON'T KNOW WHY
SHE'S TAKEN A LIKING TO ME.
- HMM.
- BUT UNTIL SHE GETS USED TO
HER NEW WAY OF LIFE HERE,
WE NEED TO HELP HER OUT
A LITTLE.
- HEY, YOSHIDA.
GOOD MORNING.
- I WAS WONDERING WHEN
YOU'D GET HERE.  GOOD MORNING.
- WHATEVER.
- HI, KONOE.
HOW ARE YOU?
- I'M FINE,
MISS YOSHIDA.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO
WAIT FOR US.
- I KNOW, BUT I COULDN'T
HELP BUT FEEL
KIND OF GUILTY
ABOUT IT ALL.
YOU WALKED WITH HER
THIS MORNING,
BUT I'M SUPPOSED TO
LOOK AFTER HER TOO.
- I TOLD YOU,
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT IT.
HER HOUSE IS ON MY WAY.  YOU
LIVE IN THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION.
- STILL THOUGH...
- I TELL YOU WHAT:
I'LL WALK HER
TO SCHOOL,
BUT GIRL STUFF--
I'LL LEAVE THAT UP TO YOU.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
- ( both chuckle )
- WE NEED TO GET GOING, OR
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE FOR CLASS.
- WELL, ARE YOU READY
TO START THE DAY?
- SURE.
- ( clock chiming )
- SINCE WHEN DOES P.E. CLASS
MEAN CLEANING THE POOL?
AREN'T THERE CHILD LABOR LAWS?
- WHO KNOWS?
WELL, I GUESS IT'S BETTER
THAN SITTING AT A DESK.
- KONOE, LOOK OUT!
- ( sighs )
MAN, THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- Tanaka: HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- YOU'RE TOO COOL TO HELP, HUH?
( laughing )
- OKAY, YOU HOLD IT
BY THE HANDLE,
THEN PUSH DOWN
AS YOU MOVE FORWARD.
- Tanaka: HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
- CAN'T CATCH ME!
- OH, YEAH?
PAYBACK!
- YOU WOULDN'T DO THAT
TO SHANA, WOULD YOU?
- ( groans )
- MM!
- TAKE THAT!
- HA-HA!  YOU MISSED ME!
- ARGH!
- Yuji: TANAKA!
- ( laughing )
- I'M GONNA GET YOU.
- Ogata: NYAH-NYAH!
- Tanaka: HEY!
- TAKE THAT!
- ( exclaims )
- ( laughs )
YEAH!
- RICE BALLS AGAIN?
YOU LIKE 'EM THAT MUCH?
- I LOVE 'EM.
RICE BALLS ARE SO TASTY.
THEY'RE MY FAVORITE FOOD.
- ( laughs )
- YOU'RE A LUCKY MAN, SAKAI.
I MEAN, TWO BOXED LUNCHES?
- ( chuckles )
SOMETHING WRONG?
WANT TO TRY SOME?
- PLEASE.
- I'M AFRAID THAT'S NOT
GONNA HAPPEN, KONOE.
THAT'S NO ORDINARY
BOXED LUNCH.
KAZUMI WORKED REALLY HARD
TO MAKE IT JUST FOR SAKAI.
- OH, SHE CAN HAVE SOME.
I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
- WELL, JUST
A LITTLE TASTE.
- IT'S DELICIOUS.
- YOU WANT TO TRY?
- YES, PLEASE.
- IS THAT OKAY?
- WHY SHOULD I CARE?
IT BELONGS TO YOU NOW.
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT WITH IT.
- WELL THEN,
HERE YOU GO.
- Yuji: WE'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW, YOSHIDA.
CAREFUL WALKING HOME.
- I WILL.
- THERE THEY GO.
YOU WANT TO GO
WITH THEM, HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU SHOULD TAG ALONG.
YOU'RE PARTIALLY
RESPONSIBLE FOR HER.
AND THEY THINK
I'M THE RESPONSIBLE ONE.
- Shana: GREAT,
NOW YOSHIDA'S DECIDED
TO WALK HOME
WITH US TOO.
I USED TO HAVE YUJI
ALL TO MYSELF.
- OH, LOOK AT THAT.
THIS RESTAURANT
IS BRAND NEW, ISN'T IT?
- Yuji: SEEMS LIKE
A COOL PLACE.
LOOK, AND IT SAYS TOMORROW'S
THEIR GRAND OPENING.
HEY, WE SHOULD GET THE GANG
TOGETHER FOR A BITE.
I THINK IT'D BE FUN.
- ME TOO.
- WHAT'S THIS?
SUPERSIZE HEAVEN?
WAIT A SEC.
WHERE DID KONOE
RUN OFF TO?
- Yuji: THERE SHE IS.
HEY, KONOE, WAIT UP!
- YOU CAN'T JUST
WANDER OFF LIKE THAT.
PERSONALLY I DON'T CARE
WHAT HAPPENS TO YOU,
BUT WE GAVE OUR WORD WE'D LOOK
AFTER YOU, SO AT LEAST TRY
TO STAY CLOSE TO US.
- JEEZ, SHANA.
- SORRY I UPSET YOU.
- YOU BIG BABY!
- Yuji: JEEZ, SHANA.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO YELL AT HER.
- FINE.
- WHAT IS IT?
- WHAT THE HECK IS SHE DOING
OVER THERE?
- Kazumi: THAT'S AMAZING.
- ( bird chirping )
- Margery: I SEE.
SO IT TURNS OUT
THAT TRANSFER STUDENT
DIDN'T HAVE A SUSPICIOUS BONE
IN HER BODY AFTER ALL.
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.  IN FACT,
I THINK IT'S SAFE TO SAY
SHE'S THE MOST HARMLESS PERSON
AT OUR SCHOOL.
- REALLY NOW?
DID YOU COME UP WITH ANYTHING?
WHAT DID OUTLAW
HAVE TO SAY ABOUT IT?
HAVE THEY
REPLIED YET?
- ( yells )
- INDEED THEY HAVE NOT,
MISS MARGERY.  THERE IS NO NEWS
REGARDING THE MOVEMENTS
OF BAL MASQUE AT THIS TIME.
- FIGURED AS MUCH.
THEIR RESEMBLANCE
IS JUST A COINCIDENCE.
WHY WOULD THEY EVER
SEND HECATE
TO A PLACE OCCUPIED
BY FLAME HAZE?
EVEN THAT FOOL BEL-PEOL
KNOWS BETTER, RIGHT?
- I DON'T--
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
WE'VE GOT TO BE MORE CAREFUL
NOW THAT WE KNOW
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
HAS A KEEPER ON IT.
- EXCUSE ME,
WHAT WAS THIS OUTLAW THING
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT?
- IT IS A SITE
WHERE FLAME HAZE GATHER
TO EXCHANGE INFORMATION
WITH ONE ANOTHER.
- Tiamat: LIKE A SUPPORT
GROUP.
- Marcosias: SINCE FLAME HAZE
LIKE WORKING SOLO, THE OUTLAW'S
THE ONLY PLACE YOU'LL FIND
A FEW HANGING AROUND.
- NOT THAT IT'S
ANY OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT DON'T YOU HAVE
MORE IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO
THAN SIT AROUND HERE
ALL DAY?
THE RUNT AND THAT MYSTES
MUST BE
IN THE MIDDLE OF TRAINING
BY NOW, RIGHT?
ARE YOU SURE IT'S OKAY
TO LEAVE THEM UNSUPERVISED?
- INDEED.
IT IS ONLY THIS ONE TIME.
- ( ice clinks )
- YEAH?
I THINK YOU MAY BE
GIVING YUJI TOO MUCH CREDIT.
- Tiamat: HE IS
PRETTY SLOW.
- WELL, IT SOUNDS
LIKE THOSE TWO
ARE GONNA HAVE
A GRAND OLD TIME TONIGHT.
I'LL HAVE A DRINK IN THEIR
HONOR.  TO SHANA AND YUJI.
- Sato:
SO SAKAI HAS BEEN TRAINING
AGAINST A FLAME HAZE
ALL THIS TIME?
- WATCH IT, SHANA.
WHY THE HECK ARE YOU BEING
SO HARD ON ME TONIGHT?
- GET UP
AND START FIGHTING!
- Shana:
WHY?
WHY DO I FEEL THIS WAY?
- Alastor: ALL RIGHT, YUJI,
I WANT YOU TO TRY AND ANTICIPATE
SHANA'S ATTACKS
THROUGH HER SHIFTING MOVEMENTS.
- ( yells )
- ( screams )
ARGH.
- YOU'VE GOT A LONG WAY TO GO.
- Alastor: YUJI SAKAI,
YOUR SENSES
ARE INCREDIBLY SHARP.
AND I CAN TELL YOU HAVE
THE EQUIVALENT
OF A CRIMSON LORD'S
POWER OF EXISTENCE WITHIN YOU.
DEPENDING ON YOUR
PROGRESS IN TRAINING,
YOU MAY FIND YOURSELF
FOLLOWING A PATH
OTHER THAN THAT OF AN ORDINARY
TORCH OR MYSTES.
KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK.
- IS THERE MORE I COULD DO?
- YOU COULD FIND YOURSELF
ON A PATH
ONLY YOU ARE CAPABLE
OF FOLLOWING.
- YOU'RE BECOMING
STRONGER, YUJI.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
LONG AS YOU KEEP WORKING HARD
WITHOUT DISTRACTIONS, THAT IS.
- WHAT'S
A "SUPERSIZE HEAVEN"?
- Sato: I HEARD
ABOUT THIS PLACE.
- Ike: I DIDN'T THINK TANAKA AND
SATO WERE GONNA COME WITH US.
- SATO'D NEVER TURN DOWN A PLACE
CALLED "SUPERSIZE HEAVEN."
- Waitress: OKAY,
SUPERSIZE CURRY,
SUPERSIZE KATSU-DON,
SUPERSIZE RAMEN
AND ANOTHER
SUPERSIZE RAMEN.
- OH, KATSU-DON,
HOW I LOVE THEE.
BUT KNOW THIS:
I WILL DESTROY YOU.
- SAKAI, I CHALLENGE YOU!
( slurping )
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO PROVE, BUT YOU'RE ON.
- HEY, SHANA, ARE YOU GONNA
EAT ALL THAT BY YOURSELF?
- WELL, I'M CERTAINLY NOT GONNA
SHARE IT WITH YOU THREE IDIOTS.
- IF YOU ASK ME,
WHAT WE ORDERED IS MORE THAN
ENOUGH FOR ONE PERSON.
- Ike: DON'T PUSH YOURSELVES
TOO HARD, GUYS.
YOU MIGHT GET SICK.
- Tanaka: COME ON, SATO!
YOU CAN TAKE HIM!
- GO EASY,
OR YOU'RE GONNA HURL.
- ( bird chirping )
- WHOA, A TIE.
- EPIC MEAL TIME.
- ( Yuji groans )
- Kazumi: YOU OKAY, SAKAI?
- Sato: DAMN IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I DIDN'T WIN.
- Kazumi: WAIT A MINUTE.
- Ike: WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- Kazumi: WHERE'S KONOE?
SHE WAS JUST HERE.
I NEVER EVEN SAW HER
LEAVE THE TABLE.
- Ike: WAS SHE IN THERE?
- HUH-UH.
WE LOOKED ALL OVER.
- WE CHECKED THE RESTROOM
AND EVERYTHING, BUT NO LUCK.
- SHE COULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN
TOO FAR FROM US, RIGHT?
- I SURE HOPE NOT.
LET'S FIND HER.
- Shana: WHY BOTHER?
- WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
YOU HAVE TO GO LOOKING FOR HER.
- WELL, BECAUSE
I'M RESPONSIBLE FOR HER.
- THAT'S ONLY
WHEN WE'RE ON CAMPUS.
- YEAH, BUT WE'RE STILL
ON OUR WAY HOME FROM SCHOOL.
AND I PROMISED
OUR TEACHER
THAT I'D MAKE SURE
SHE ARRIVES SAFELY.
- WE'VE ALREADY WARNED KONOE
NOT TO WANDER OFF.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
WE'VE DONE ALL WE NEED TO,
AND IT'S NOT OUR FAULT
SHE GOT LOST.
- SHANA.
- SEE YOU.
- SHANA, WAIT UP!
WHAT ARE YOU
SO ANGRY ABOUT?
- I'M NOT ANGRY
ABOUT ANYTHING.
- DON'T LIE TO ME.
- I'M NOT LYING.
IT'S JUST THAT I--
- THAT YOU WHAT?
SHANA.
- I WISH YOU'D JUST
FORGET ABOUT HER.
- WHERE'S THIS HATRED
COMING FROM?
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S
A DENIZEN OR ANYTHING.
- IT'S NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT.
THE TRUTH OF IT IS...
- TELL ME.
- NO.
- WOW, I FEEL LIKE
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
- DON'T BE SO HARD
ON YOURSELF, KAZUMI.
- I THINK WE SHOULD SPLIT UP
AND LOOK FOR HER.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- MAYBE THAT'S
WHERE SHE IS.
- KONOE!
- ( cat screeches )
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- ( chirping )
- DID YOU SAVE IT
FROM THAT STRAY CAT?
- LOOK, AND HE'S
FINE NOW.
- STILL CAN'T GET OVER
HOW MUCH SHE LOOKS LIKE HER.
- ARE YOU--?
- I SHOULD PROBABLY
PUREE THE CARROTS NEXT.
WHY AM I FEELING
SO JEALOUS OF HER?
I DON'T LIKE THIS FEELING,
NOT ONE BIT.
- I WONDER
WHERE SHANA IS.
- I'M SORRY, THE MISTRESS
IS NOT COMING TONIGHT.
I AM YOUR
SPARRING PARTNER
UNTIL MILADY SEES FIT
TO CONTINUE YOUR TRAINING.
- ( Fumina giggles )
- FROM WHAT
I COULD TELL,
THE BIRDS REALLY LIKED
THEIR NEW HOUSE.
- HOW COME SHANA ISN'T
WALKING WITH US?
- UH, IT'S A LONG STORY.
- Yuji:
SHANA DIDN'T SHOW UP
FOR MORNING TRAINING EITHER.
GUESS SHE'S STILL ANGRY WITH ME.
JUST WISH
I KNEW WHY.
- OH.
GOOD MORNING, YOSHIDA.
- ARE YOU HAVING
A GOOD DAY TODAY?
- I AM,
THANK YOU, KONOE.
- 'MORNING.
- SHANA?
AWKWARD.
- ( clock chiming )
- HERE YOU GO.
- THANKS.
- YOSHIDA HAD TO GO TO
A LIBRARY COMMITTEE MEETING.
- SHANA.
- AGAIN WITH
THE RICE BALLS.
- Yuji: I WONDER WHAT'S REALLY
BOTHERING SHANA.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji:
SHANA'S EMOTIONS ARE IN TURMOIL,
AND IT'S ALL
BECAUSE OF KONOE.
WILHELMINA IS
COMPLETELY CONFUSED,
AND IT'S PUTTING A STRAIN
ON THEIR RELATIONSHIP.
ALL IT TOOK
WAS ONE LITTLE TIFF,
AND NOW SHE'S
ON SHANA'S BAD SIDE.
UNABLE TO FIGURE IT OUT
ON HER OWN,
WILHELMINA LOOKS TO MY MOM,
CHIGUSA, FOR HELP.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"THE FAMILY DINNER TABLE."