- ( theme song playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( wind whistling )
- ( jingles )
- Mare: A TRANSIENT
AND YET ETERNAL AFFAIR.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( car horns honking )
- ( people chattering )
- Yuji: THAT MORNING BEGAN
JUST LIKE ANY OTHER.
I WAS OFF TO MEET MY BEST FRIEND
FROM MIDDLE SCHOOL,
HAYATO IKE,
BEFORE CLASS.
IT FELT TOO NORMAL
TO BE MY LAST MORNING.
- ( students chattering )
- SAKAI.
- IKE.
WHAT'S UP?
- Hayato: WITH YOU AROUND,
IT DOESN'T FEEL
LIKE I'M IN HIGH SCHOOL,
YOU KNOW?
IT'S JUST LIKE
THE OLD DAYS.
- THAT'S NOT
SUCH A BAD THING, IS IT?
SO ARE YOU FREE
AFTER SCHOOL TODAY?
- NO, I'VE GOT TO GO
TO CRAM SCHOOL.
- JEEZ, YOU'RE ALREADY
PREPARING FOR COLLEGE?
- I'VE GOT TO DO WHAT I CAN
TO KEEP MY PARENTS HAPPY.
OTHERWISE MY ALLOWANCE
ENDS UP SUFFERING.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- I GUESS I'LL GO DOWN
TO THE STATION
AND CHECK OUT THE NEW
CD RELEASES.
UH, HOLD ON.
- HMM?
- IKE, DON'T YOU FEEL
LIKE WE'VE HAD
THIS CONVERSATION BEFORE?
CHERRY BLOSSOMS?
BUT IT'S SEPTEMBER,
RIGHT?
- YEAH, SO?
- THAT'S WEIRD.
OH, WELL.
- Yuji:
THIS IS OUR SECOND SEMESTER.
ALL THE CRAZY STUFF THAT
HAPPENED OVER SUMMER VACATION
HAS LONG SINCE BEEN
FORGOTTEN.
- ( panting )
SAKAI.
HAVING A GOOD MORNING?
- YEAH, THANKS.
- HMM.
- YOSHIDA SURE HAS CHANGED.
SHE'S MUCH MORE CONFIDENT
THAN BEFORE.
- Hayato: YOSHIDA?
IF YOU'RE FREE
AT SOME POINT TODAY,
WOULD YOU MIND
HELPING ME PREPARE
FOR TOMORROW'S
STUDENT COUNCIL MEETING?
- SURE, NO PROBLEM.
IT'D BE HARD
TO DO THAT
ALL ON YOUR OWN.
- I APPRECIATE IT.
- IKE HAS DECLARED WAR IN
THE BATTLE FOR YOSHIDA'S HEART.
- ( yawns )
MAN, I'M STILL
SO FREAKIN' SLEEPY.
- I'VE HEARD THAT MARGERY'S
STILL STAYING AT SATO'S HOUSE
AND EVIDENTLY SHE'S REFUSING
TO CHANGE HER WAYS.
- ( giggles )
( giggles )
- SEE YA.
- Yuji: AND THEN THERE'S HER.
- QUIT FOLLOWING ME,
WILHELMINA.
I ALREADY TOLD YOU, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WALK ME TO SCHOOL.
- I DO NOT MEAN
TO BE A BOTHER, MILADY.
I SIMPLY WISH TO DETERMINE
WHETHER OR NOT YOUR SCHOOL
IS UP TO STANDARD.
- Tiamat: WE WANT A TOUR.
- WHY CAN'T YOU WAIT
UNTIL I INVITE YOU
TO A CULTURAL FESTIVAL
OR SOMETHING?
GO HOME.
( grunts )
- ( sighs )
I WILL LEAVE
ON ONE CONDITION:
YOU MUST PROMISE TO ALERT ME
WHEN SUCH A FESTIVAL ARISES.
- Tiamat: UNTIL THEN.
- YUJI.
- ( Yuji's voice )
SOME THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
SHANA AND I ARE STILL
ALIVE AND WELL IN MISAKI CITY.
- ( students chattering )
- NOW YOU KIDS
WILL WANT TO TAKE NOTES.
- Yuji: SHANA DOESN'T
SEEM FAZED BY WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT I CAN'T STOP THINKING
ABOUT THAT DAY.
RIGHT BEFORE WE THOUGHT
WE WERE GOING TO DISAPPEAR,
SHE SAID SOMETHING
TO ME.
- TENPA JYOUSAI.
I SHOULD TELL YOU...
YUJI, I--
- FOR SOME REASON
I CAN'T SEEM TO REMEMBER
WHAT SHE SAID
AFTER THAT.
- ( inaudible )
- DID SHE TELL ME SHE--?
NO, I MUST BE CRAZY.
THERE'S NO WAY SHANA FEELS
THAT WAY ABOUT ME.
- ( thud )
- THAT'S IT, HIRAI.
WHY ARE YOU JUST
SITTING THERE
WITHOUT YOUR NOTEBOOK
OR TEXTBOOK OPEN?
IF YOU'RE SO SMART,
FILL IN THE BLANK FOR US.
- YEAH, FINE.
- HUH?
- BUT I SHOULD
TELL YOU, SIR,
YOUR LITTLE FILL-IN-THE-BLANK
QUESTION IS LAUGHABLE.
WE'RE NOT PARTICIPATING
IN SOME SILLY GAME SHOW,
THEREFORE THE ANSWER SHOULDN'T
BE SO OVERWHELMINGLY OBVIOUS.
THE COMPLETED LINE IS,
"THAT WHICH WE CALL A ROSE,
BY ANY OTHER NAME
WOULD SMELL AS SWEET."
IT'S A LINE FROM
WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE'S
"ROMEO AND JULIET."
SEEING AS YOU'VE CHOSEN
TO LEAVE IN THE WORDS "ROSE"
AND "AS SWEET," THE ONLY
VIABLE OPTION FOR THE BLANK...
- WHY DO I FEEL LIKE
THIS HAS HAPPENED BEFORE?
- ( gasps ) WOW,
YOU MADE THOSE, KAZUMI?
THEY LOOK SUPER YUMMY.
- THEY LOOK AMAZING.
- ( chuckles )
- DELICIOUS.
- YOURS TASTE SO MUCH BETTER
THAN WHAT'S SOLD IN STORES.
- YOU REALLY
THINK SO, IKE?
- ( chuckles )
- ( wind whistling )
- IT'S STRANGE.
I KEEP GETTING THIS FEELING
THAT ALL THIS
HAS ALREADY HAPPENED.
IT'S LIKE DEJA VU.
- THEY'RE HERE.
- IT'S A SEAL.
- HOW DO YOU DO,
DEAR YOUNG LADY?
I WONDERED WHEN WE WOULD
FINALLY MEET FACE TO FACE.
- IT'S FRIAGNE THE HUNTER.
BUT NO, THAT CAN'T BE.
SHANA, WHAT IS THIS?
- I GUESS YOU MUST BE
THAT RINNE'S MASTER.
- YES, YOU MAY CALL HER
MARIANNE.
I AM FRIAGNE THE HUNTER.
ISN'T THIS EXCITING,
GETTING TO MEET YOU IN PERSON,
ALASTOR,
THE FLAME OF HEAVEN?
- Alastor: I CAN'T SAY
THAT I'M THRILLED.
- BUT THEY HAVE MET.
THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE!
- AN INTERESTING CHOICE
OF CONTRACTOR--
THE FLAMING-HAIRED,
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
I'VE HEARD
OF YOUR STRENGTH.
- JUST TRY ME.
- ARGH!
- MY, IT WOULD APPEAR
THE TALES I'VE HEARD WERE TRUE.
- Yuji:
WHY IS FRIAGNE HERE?
HE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE DEAD.
SHANA AND ALASTOR
DON'T SEEM BOTHERED BY IT.
BUT WHY NOT?
- ( screams )
- NOT AGAIN.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED
BEFORE.  WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( bells jingle )
- HUH?
HUH.  BELLS?
- ( screams )
( screaming )
MASTER, I'M SO SORRY
I'VE FAILED YOU.
- THERE'S NO NEED
TO APOLOGIZE, MARIANNE.
THAT FLAME HAZE IS A BRUTE.
I'LL RETURN.
AND THEN I'LL CLAIM
MY PRIZE.
AFTER ALL, THIS IS
MY HUNTING GROUND.
- SHANA, WILL YOU
PLEASE EXPLAIN?
WHY IS FRIAGNE
STILL ALIVE?
- HE CALLED THIS
HIS HUNTING GROUND.
HE MUST BE THE REASON THERE ARE
SO MANY TORCHES IN THIS CITY.
- Alastor: YES.
I WOULD VENTURE TO GUESS
IT'S ALL PART OF HIS PLAN.
- HE'S INSANE.
- SHANA, WOULD YOU LISTEN
TO WHAT I'M ASKING YOU?
WHY DID FRIAGNE SHOW UP HERE
WHEN HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE DEAD?
IT'S LIKE THE PAST
IS REPEATING ITSELF.
CAN'T YOU FEEL IT?
- I NEED TO REBUILD
BEFORE LEAVING THE SEAL.
- ( bells jingle )
- Yuji: WE SPENT THE REST OF THE
SCHOOL DAY
LEARNING THINGS
WE'D ALREADY COVERED.
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
- Hayato: WHAT'S UP, SAKAI?
ARE YOU HEADED HOME?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- CAN YOU TELL ME
WHAT MONTH IT IS RIGHT NOW?
- WHAT?  IT'S SEPTEMBER,
YOU BIG DUMMY.
- BUT CHERRY BLOSSOMS
USUALLY BLOOM IN THE SPRINGTIME,
DON'T THEY?
- I'VE GOT TO DO WHAT I CAN
TO KEEP MY PARENTS HAPPY.
OTHERWISE MY ALLOWANCE
ENDS UP SUFFERING.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
BYE.
- WAIT.
WILHELMINA, THANK GOODNESS
IT'S YOU.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
MASTER YUJI?
HAS SOMETHING HAPPENED
TO THE MISTRESS?
- YEAH, BUT IT'S NOT
JUST SHANA.
I'M NOT SURE
WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT DENIZENS WE'VE ALREADY
DEFEATED ARE SHOWING BACK UP.
IT'S LIKE HISTORY
IS REPEATING ITSELF.
HAVE YOU NOTICED ANYTHING
OUT OF THE ORDINARY?
- I MUST BE GOING.
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO WALK THE MISTRESS HOME.
- Tiamat: SCHOOL IS OUT
FOR THE DAY.
- WILHELMINA, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WALK ME HOME EITHER.
- I WAS IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
MILADY.
- FINE.
- YUJI, YOU'D BETTER NOT BE
LATE FOR TRAINING TODAY.
- Tiamat: BE PUNCTUAL.
- WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON?
EVERYONE'S ACTING
STRANGELY.
- ( bells jingle )
- I HEAR BELLS AGAIN.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHERE ARE THEY
COMING FROM?
THIS IS TOO BIZARRE.
IT MUST BE THE WORK
OF A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
BUT WHAT EXACTLY
ARE THEY UP TO?
COULD IT BE
AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL?
WAIT.  YEAH,
MARGERY WOULD KNOW.
IF I REMEMBER
CORRECTLY,
SATO'S HOUSE
IS IN HAGINO-CHOU.
BUT I'VE NEVER
ACTUALLY BEEN THERE.
- ( bells jingling )
- ( Mare laughing )
- ( moaning )
- I'VE GOT TO TRY
TO CALM DOWN.
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO REALIZES
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
IF ANYBODY'S GONNA GET US
OUT OF THIS, IT'S GONNA BE ME.
BUT...
AM I GONNA BE ABLE
TO DO THIS ON MY OWN?
I'VE ALWAYS RELIED
ON SHANA FOR HELP,
BUT THIS TIME
SHE'S BEEN AFFECTED TOO.
ANY DENIZEN WHO'S CAPABLE
OF PULLING THIS OFF
HAS GOT TO BE
PRETTY STRONG.
BUT IF IT IS
THAT POWERFUL,
THEN I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY NOBODY ELSE
HAS BEEN ABLE
TO PICK UP ON IT?
I MEAN, EVEN IF IT IS USING
AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL,
SHANA AND THE OTHER FLAME HAZE
WOULD HAVE SENSED ITS PRESENCE.
THERE'S NO WAY IT WOULD HAVE
GOTTEN PAST HER.
EXACTLY.
SHE WOULD HAVE NOTICED IT.
SO THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
WAIT, MAYBE I SHOULD
APPROACH THIS DIFFERENTLY.
WHAT IF IT HAS LESS TO DO
WITH HER AND MORE WITH ME?
WHAT IF I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S NOTICED, BECAUSE--
THAT'S GOT TO BE IT.
- ( knocks on door )
- ( door opens )
YUJI, HON, I JUST MADE COFFEE.
WOULD YOU LIKE A CUP?
- MOM.
- HMM?
- IS IT THE SAME COFFEE
YOU ALWAYS MAKE?
- YES, IT IS.
YOU LIKE IT, DON'T YOU?
- THIS MAY SEEM LIKE
A WEIRD QUESTION TO ASK,
BUT COULD YOU TELL ME
WHERE YOU BOUGHT THAT COFFEE?
- YOUR DAD CALLED ME
THIS MORNING
AND HE SAID HE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT HOME SOON.
- ( both giggling )
- ( panting )
- SHANA!
- HERE YOU ARE,
DEAR BROTHER.
IT'S THE NIETONO NO SHANA
YOU'VE BEEN LONGING FOR.
- YAY.
- IF I'M RIGHT,
I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO STOP THEM MYSELF.
IT'S WHY FRIAGNE SHOWED UP,
EVEN THOUGH I KNOW HE'S DEAD,
AND WHY I COULDN'T GO
TO SATO'S HOUSE.
IT'S THE REASON
THINGS FROM THE PAST
KEEP HAPPENING AGAIN.
I GET IT NOW.
- ( exclaims )
- IT'S THE ONLY THING
THAT MAKES SENSE,
SO I BET
I CAN DO THIS...
- STOP IT.
LEAVE HER ALONE.
- HE IS A FOOL,
DEAR BROTHER.
YOU HAVE
THE POWER NOW.
YOU CAN GO KILL HIM
IF YOU WANT TO.
- SHANA'S COMPLETELY HELPLESS
IN THIS SITUATION,
SO I GUESS
IT'S ALL UP TO ME.
JUST TO TEST
MY THEORY,
I WONDER IF I CAN REMEMBER
WHAT SHE SAID TO ME THAT DAY.
- YUJI, I...
- NO, ALL THAT CAN EXIST HERE
IS STUFF I ALREADY KNOW.
I CAN'T GO ANYWHERE
I'VE NEVER BEEN BEFORE.
AND NO ONE CAN
ANSWER QUESTIONS
I DON'T ALREADY
KNOW THE ANSWER TO.
BECAUSE ALL OF THIS
IS A WORLD THAT I CREATED.
- ( giggling )
- ( bells jingling )
- A TRANSIENT
AND YET ETERNAL AFFAIR.
- THIS IS ALL
A DREAM!
- YUJI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- SHANA.
- YOU CAN'T SPACE OUT
IN THE MIDDLE OF A FIGHT.
- SORRY.
HOW LONG WAS I ASLEEP?
- Alastor: FOR NO MORE
THAN A FEW SECONDS.
BUT EVEN THAT'S
DANGEROUS IN BATTLE.
YOU CAN TAKE YOUR NAP
WHEN WE'RE DONE.
- DAMN IT,
YOU'VE GOT TO PAY ATTENTION.
- YEAH, YEAH, RIGHT.
THERE'S THE SHANA
I KNOW.
- YOU'RE NOT SLEEPWALKING,
ARE YOU?  NO MATTER HOW WEAK
THE DENIZEN MAY BE,
YOU CAN'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
SHE HAS A VERY POWERFUL
TREASURE TOOL.
- YOU THINK SHE'S WEAK?
- WELCOME BACK, MYSTES.
HOW WAS YOUR
TRANSIENT DREAM?
( giggles )
- ( bells jingle )
- NOT TOO SMART,
SHOWING YOURSELF TO ME.
I CAN EASILY OVERPOWER YOU.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN WIN.
- MAYBE NOT,
BUT I HAVE NO PROBLEM
RISKING MY LIFE
TO GET WHAT I WANT.
AS A CRIMSON DENIZEN, I'M FREE
TO DO WHATEVER I PLEASE,
LONG AS I'M NOT CAUGHT.
- PARTY'S OVER.
YOU'VE BEEN CAUGHT.
( shouts )
- ( bells jingle )
- ( giggling )
- THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE ENCOUNTERED
SUCH AN INCREDIBLY WEAK
CRIMSON DENIZEN.
- Alastor: HMM, HAD IT NOT
SHOWN ITSELF,
WE MAY NEVER HAVE EVEN
REALIZED IT WAS HERE.
- IT MAY HAVE BEEN WEAK,
BUT IT HAD A STRANGE POWER.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LIKE PUTTING YOU TO SLEEP
IN THE MIDDLE OF BATTLE?
- WELL, I THINK.
WAIT.
I JUST COMPLETELY FORGOT
WHAT I WAS GONNA SAY.
WHAT WAS IT?
- JEEZ, YOU ARE
SLEEPWALKING.
- Alastor: YOU'VE GOT TO STAY
ON TOP OF YOUR GAME, YUJI SAKAI.
DON'T FORGET
THAT YOU HAVE
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
TREASURE TOOL INSIDE OF YOU.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHEN BAL MASQUE
MIGHT COME AFTER YOU
TO STEAL IT FOR THEMSELVES.
- Yuji: I KNOW.
- OKAY, LET'S GO
TO SCHOOL.
- MM-HMM.
- UM, SHANA, I--
- GO ON.
- WELL, I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO ASK YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
REMEMBER WHEN WE THOUGHT
WE WERE GONNA DISAPPEAR?
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO ME
RIGHT BEFORE THE BLAST HAPPENED?
- ( Alastor gulps )
- HUH?  I--
I DON'T REMEMBER.
I PROBABLY THANKED YOU
FOR FIGHTING ALONGSIDE ME.
- I DEFINITELY HEARD YOU SAY
MY NAME, BUT THAT'S ABOUT IT.
- I-- I SAID
I RESPECT YOU.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
NOW WHAT?
- SO THAT'S ALL?
- SHUT UP, SHUT UP
SHUT UP!
WHAT I SAID
ISN'T IMPORTANT.
- IT CERTAINLY SOUNDED
LIKE IT WAS.
- HA!
WELL, NOT IMPORTANT ENOUGH
FOR ME TO REMEMBER.
- Yuji: IF YOU SAY SO.
- ( Alastor chuckles )
- Yuji: I SHOULD
JUST LEAVE HER ALONE.
THERE'S NO WAY
SHE SAID--
- GOOD MORNING.
- HUH?  OH, HEY THERE.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU TOO.
- YO, WHAT'S UP?
- OH, I DIDN'T SEE YOU, IKE.
- GOOD MORNING.
- I DID IT BECAUSE
I LOVE YOU, SAKAI.
- HEY, ABOUT YOSHIDA--
NEXT TERM I'M COMPETING
FOR HER HEART.
- GUESS THIS IS
ROUND TWO, HUH?
- AND THIS TIME
I'M SERIOUS.
- YEAH, WELL, SO AM I.
SO WATCH OUT.
- OW, MY HEAD HURTS
SO BAD.
WHY WON'T YOU DO SOMETHING
TO HELP ME OUT?
I'M GONNA THROW UP.
- Marcosias: I TOLD YOU TO STOP.
I SWEAR, YOU'RE LIKE
A BOTTOMLESS PIT WITH THE BOOZE,
MARGERY.  YOU JUST KEEP
GOING AND GOING.
I'M DONE
BABYSITTING YOU.
- STOP YELLING AT ME, MARCO.
- HEY MARGERY.
I BROUGHT YOU SOME WATER.
IT'S ON THE TABLE.
I'LL GET YOU SOME HANGOVER
MEDICINE ON THE WAY HOME.
- WELL, HURRY,
'CAUSE I'M DYING OVER HERE.
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
BE BACK SOON.
- Ogata: THE WEATHER'S
AWESOME TODAY, HUH?
- Tanaka: YEAH,
BEAUTIFUL WEATHER.
- ( bells jingling )
- ( Mare laughing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE MYSTERIOUS DREAM
I THOUGHT I HAD WOKEN UP FROM
STARTS ALL OVER AGAIN.
BUT THIS TIME I'M NOT THE ONLY
ONE WHO GETS PULLED IN.
SHANA AND YOSHIDA
ARE TOO.
SHANA AND I DESPERATELY TRY TO
FIND A WAY OUT OF THE NIGHTMARE.
WHO COULD POSSIBLY BE
MANIPULATING OUR DREAMS?
IT SEEMS THAT BEL-PEOL,
SYDONAY AND HECATE
ARE READY TO MAKE
THEIR NEXT MOVE.
BAL MASQUE BEGINS
A NEW PLOT.
NEXT TIME ON
"SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"THE BEGINNING
OF EVERYTHING."