- Alastor:
WHILE YUJI SAKAI AND HIS FRIENDS
WERE BUSY PREPARING
FOR THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL,
WILHELMINA WAS INVESTIGATING
PHELES AND JOHAN,
KNOWN AS THE ENGAGED LINK.
WHEN YUJI REVEALED
HE'D CAST A SILVER SEAL,
WILHELMINA MADE A PLEA
TO PHELES,
BUT TOO LATE, AS HER WIND HAS
ALREADY BLOWN INTO TOWN.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( wind howling )
- ( grunting )
- FEELS GOOD TO GET A LITTLE
TRAINING IN.  IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
- IF WE TAKE TOO MUCH TIME OFF,
YOU'LL LOSE ALL YOUR PROGRESS.
- Alastor: WITH YOUR TRAINING
LIMITED TO MANEUVERS,
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
WON'T SUSPECT ANYTHING.
- IS THERE A REASON WILHELMINA
DIDN'T JOIN US?
- YES, SHE'S BUSY INVESTIGATING
THE CAUSE OF YOUR SILVER FLAME.
I'M AFRAID THIS IS A MYSTERY
THAT WILL NOT BE EASY TO SOLVE,
BUT I HAVE NO DOUBT
THAT WILHELMINA CARMEL
IS UP TO THE TASK.
WE'LL LET HER BREAK THE NEWS
TO THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- OKAY.
- I WANT YOU TO PROMISE ME
WHEN YOU MAKE A DECISION,
I'LL BE THE FIRST TO KNOW.
- BUT, SHANA.
I PROMISE.
NO MATTER WHAT,
I'LL BE HERE FOR YOU.
AFTER ALL OUR WORK, I'M GLAD
THE FESTIVAL'S FINALLY STARTING.
( gasps )
- COME ON.  LET'S GO.
- HEY, SHANA.  WAIT UP!
- I DON'T THINK WE'LL BE ABLE
TO KEEP THIS INFORMATION
FROM THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
FOR LONG.
- Tiamat:
YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
- WE'RE GOING TO
NEED HER ASSISTANCE
IF PHELES COMES LOOKING
FOR THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
INDEED, SHOULD THE MYSTES
BE RELATED TO THE SILVER?
EVEN MORE SO.
- AGREED.
- AN ENCOUNTER WITH THE SILVER
IS WHAT PROMPTED HER
TO ENTER
INTO A FLAME HAZE CONTRACT.
I WONDER HOW SHE'LL RESPOND
WHEN SHE FINDS OUT.
- WE'LL BE CAREFUL.
- WILL YOU MAKE SURE
THE TENT'S TIED DOWN?
HOW COME THE FOOD
ISN'T HERE YET?
ALL RIGHT, PEOPLE,
GET A MOVE ON!
- HAVE THEY FINISHED
BUILDING THE STAGE?
- HURRY!  WE DON'T HAVE LONG
TILL THE OPENING PARADE STARTS.
- Girl: WOW!
- ( crowd gasping )
- I LIKE YOUR DRESS
IT SUITS YOU.
- OH, DO YOU THINK SO?
WELL, I THINK YOU
LOOK VERY HANDSOME.
- YEAH, I DON'T KNOW
IF I'D GO THAT FAR.
- AWWWW!  SHE'S SO CUTE.
- I THINK YOU'RE A SHOO-IN
FOR THE GRAND PRIZE, SHANA.
- YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.  I THINK
YOU'VE GOT A REALLY GOOD CHANCE
OF WINNING.
YOU'D BETTER START WORKING
ON YOUR ACCEPTANCE SPEECH NOW.
- WORK ON MY WHAT?
- YOUR SPEECH.  YOU GET TO SAY
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO.
- LIKE IF THERE'S SOMETHING YOU
WANNA SAY TO SAKAI FOR INSTANCE,
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE TO DO IT.
- THIS IS MY CHANCE.
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE ABOUT TO
FALL ASLEEP ON YOUR FEET THERE.
- I HAD TO PULL ANOTHER
ALL-NIGHTER YESTERDAY.
I'D TAKE A NAP, BUT THIS
COSTUME'S HARD TO MOVE IN.
- YEAH, WELL, YOU CAN SLEEP
WHEN THE FESTIVAL'S OVER.
- SO FUNNY I FORGOT TO LAUGH.
- POKE, POKE.
- HUH?  OH.
- I'M GLAD KAZUMI AND SHANA
ENDED UP WITH THOSE ROLES.
THEY LOOK GREAT, DON'T THEY?
- YEAH, NOT TOO BAD,
BUT I GOTTA SAY,
YOU WOULD'VE MADE A BETTER
DOROTHY OR JULIET.
- OH, STOP IT.
- NO, I WAS BEING SERIOUS.
HEY, SATO, DO YOU THINK
MARGERY'S GONNA SHOW UP
TO THE PARADE?
I SURE HOPE SO.
- ( growls )
- YOU'RE JUST GONNA STAND THERE
STARING AT ME, AREN'T YOU?
- ( fireworks popping )
- Man over PA: WELCOME TO MISAKI
HIGH SCHOOL'S AUTUMN FESTIVAL.
- ( cheering )
- CHECK OUT THE GIRL DRESSED
AS ALICE IN WONDERLAND.
I BET SHE WINS.
- HEY, HOTTIE.
- ( laughing )
- ARE YOU WELL ENOUGH
TO WALK THE PARADE ROUTE?
IT'S LONG.
- I KNOW,
BUT I FEEL BETTER NOW
SO I'LL BE OKAY.
- Ogata: GUESS IKE'S THE ONLY
ONE WE GOTTA WORRY ABOUT.
THE PARADE ROUTE GOES ALL
THROUGH THE SHOPPING DISTRICT,
TO MISAKI STATION
AND THEN BACK AGAIN.
- WILL HE BE ABLE
TO WALK ALL THAT WAY?
- HECK, WILL HE BE ABLE
TO STAY ALIVE?
- It's time
for the opening parade.
- ALL RIGHT,
HERE WE GO, GUYS.
- LET'S HAVE
A GOOD TIME OUT THERE
AND TAKE HOME THE GRAND PRIZE.
- YEAH!
- KILL ME NOW.
- A BEAUTIFUL SEASON INDEED.
- Tiamat: THE FOLIAGE IS LOVELY.
- WE WERE JUST ADMIRING IT.
YOU CARE TO JOIN?
- SO YOU WANNA TELL ME
WHY YOU'RE HERE?
- JEEZ, WHAT'S GOT
YOU ALL WOUND UP?
CAN I OFFER YOU A DRINK?
IT'LL CALM YOUR NERVES.
- WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
- JULIET IS SO PRETTY.
SHE LOOKS JUST LIKE A MODEL.
- OH, LOOK HOW CUTE DOROTHY IS.
- ( laughing )
- HEY, YOU'RE NOT TIRED
OF WALKING YET, ARE YOU?
- NO, I'M FINE
THANK YOU FOR ASKING.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE GONNA
MAKE IT THROUGH THIS, BUDDY?
- YEAH, IF YOU GET TIRED, IKE,
LET US KNOW AND WE CAN CARRY YOU
THE REST OF THE WAY.
- THANKS, BUT I'LL BE OKAY.
- Konoe: YOU GUYS CAN CARRY ME.
- OUR BOY'S GOT A TOUGH DECISION
AHEAD OF HIM.
I SURE WOULDN'T WANT
TO BE IN HIS SHOES.
- ( laughs )
- LOOKS LIKE MARGERY'S
NOT GONNA MAKE IT, HUH?
- SHE STARTED DRINKING AS SOON
AS SHE WOKE UP THIS MORNING.
SHE'S GOTTA BE PASSED OUT
BY NOW.
- TALKING ABOUT THE CHANTER--
I MEAN, ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT MARGERY?
- YEAH, SHE NO-SHOWED ON US.
- SHE'S HERE.
SHE CAME ALONG WITH WILHELMINA.
- HUH?
YEAH, SEE?  RIGHT THERE.
- SHE MADE IT.
- I'M NOT LEAVING YOUR SIDE
UNTIL YOU TELL ME EVERYTHING
YOU KNOW.
- THE INFORMATION ISN'T
ABOUT HIM EXCLUSIVELY.
- I SAID EVERYTHING.
- I THINK IT'S BEST WE WAIT.
I WOULD LIKE
THE FLAME OF HEAVEN,
THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER
AND THE MYSTES TO BE PRESENT
WHEN INDEED WE FINALLY
DISCUSS THE MATTER.
- Marcosias: WHY ARE YOU BEATING
AROUND THE BUSH?
- Tiamat: NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
- HOW LONG ARE WE TALKING?
- WHY DON'T WE MEET
WITH YOU TOMORROW NIGHT?
- Margery:
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
DID YOU BRING ME HERE JUST
TO TEASE ME WITH INFORMATION?
- NO, I BROUGHT YOU HERE
TO SHOW YOU INFORMATION
IS NOT WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
- I'M SO TIRED.
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- QUIT COMPLAINING
AND PERK UP, GUYS.
- YOU WANNA IMPRESS MARGERY,
DON'T YOU?
- IKE, THAT GOES FOR YOU TOO,
HEAR ME?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE SO BOSSY.
- HEY!
I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT WE MAY NEVER HAVE
ANOTHER CHANCE TO WALK
IN A PARADE LIKE THIS AGAIN.
IT'S A SPECIAL MOMENT
AND I THINK WE SHOULD MAKE
THE MOST OF IT.
- OGATA'S RIGHT.
I MAY HAVE PROBLEMS,
BUT I'M GONNA FACE THEM.
I NEED TO MAKE THE MOST
OF EVERY MOMENT.
- ( laughing )
- YAY!
- Marcosias: THIS WAS A CHEAP
TRICK, SPECIALIST.
YOU KNEW DEEP DOWN MARGERY'S
A SOFTIE AND THE BEST WAY
TO GET AT HER IS TO TUG
AT HER HEARTSTRINGS-- OW!
- THAT'S ENOUGH OUT OF YOU.
ALL RIGHT, FINE, I'LL GIVE
YOU UNTIL TOMORROW NIGHT.
BUT I WANT EVERYTHING LAID OUT
ON THE TABLE.
NO SECRECY.  GOT ME?
- THANK YOU, CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- THE PARADE HAS MADE IT BACK
TO CAMPUS.
- ( CHEERING )
- THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE ONE LAST
LAP AROUND THE FIELD.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE TO PICK
YOUR FAVORITE COSTUMES
TO NOMINATE FOR THE GRAND PRIZE.
- MAN, I'VE NEVER BEEN
SO EXHAUSTED.
- AT LEAST YOU'RE NOT COVERED
IN FUR LIKE ME.
- DO NOT EVEN GO THERE.
- ( sighs )
- CHECK OUT SAKAI.  HE DOESN'T
EVEN LOOK LIKE HE'S BEEN
FAZED BY ALL THIS WALKING.
GUY'S GOT SOME STAMINA.
- Yuji:
YOU ALL RIGHT, IKE?
IT'S ALMOST OVER.
- COOL.  I THINK I CAN WALK
THE LAST STRETCH ON MY OWN.
- ( shouting )
- YOU'RE THE CUTEST DOROTHY
I'VE EVER SEEN, SHANA.
- YOU LOOKED SO BEAUTIFUL
OUT THERE, KAZUMI.
- OUR CLASS IS SURE
TO WIN THE GRAND PRIZE.
- SAKAI, YOU LOOK SO HANDSOME
AS ROMEO.
I BET YOU'LL WIN FOR THE BOYS.
- EVERYBODY QUIT PUSHING.
I'M GETTING CRUSHED.
- HEY, YOU GUYS, IKE'S NOT
GOOD WITH CROWDS.
- I CAN'T HANDLE IT!
( sighs )
- ( all laughing )
- HERE, ONE BLUEBERRY CREPE.
- MAN, THIS SUCKS.  THEY GOT US
WORKING LIKE DOGS BACK HERE.
- I KNOW IT'S ROUGH, BUT
SOMEBODY HAD TO COVER FOR IKE
SO HE COULD GET SOME REST.
WE'RE RUNNING KIND OF
LOW ON BATTER.
CAN SOMEONE GET MORE?
- NO PROB.
I'LL BE BACK IN A SEC.
MARGERY.
- LOOK, I'M REALLY NOT IN THE
MOOD FOR THIS RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
- COME ON, LIVE A LITTLE.
- WILHELMINA, HI.
- YOU BROUGHT HER HERE?
- YOU MEAN A LOT TO THEM
AND THEY MEAN A LOT TO ME.
THIS WAY, EVERYONE'S HAPPY,
RIGHT?
AND TO BE HONEST, I WAS KIND OF
HOPING WE MIGHT GET THE CHANCE
TO HANG OUT TOGETHER.
- Shana: HERE.
- YOU MADE THIS FOR ME,
MILADY?
- YES, INDEED.
- IT IS DELICIOUS.
- ( sighs ) I'M GONNA GO.
- OH, NO.  WE'VE COMPLETELY
RUN OUT OF BATTER.
- ON IT.
- SORRY FOR THE WAIT,
BUT IT SHOULDN'T TAKE HIM LONG.
- WE APPRECIATE YOUR PATIENCE,
GUYS.
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HAVE A TASTE?
- IT'S TOO SWEET,
BUT...
I GUESS THE MESS
IS PART OF THE FUN.
- ( cheering )
- ALL RIGHT, YOU GOT THIS!
- UGH!
- ( cheering )
- NICE!
- Yuji: YOU FEELING
BETTER NOW, IKE?
- YEAH, I REALLY
NEEDED THAT NAP.
- I'M GONNA TAKE IT EASY
THE REST OF THE DAY,
THOUGH IT'S NICE
AND QUIET IN HERE.
- IKE, I NEED YOUR HELP.
EVERYBODY'S HOURS FOR
THE GYM ARE MIXED UP.
- ( groaning )
- HE CAN'T ESCAPE HER.
THE POOR GUY.
- IF I TRULY WANT TO BE CLOSE
TO HIM.
- IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL.
LISTEN TO YOUR HEART.
IT'LL TELL YOU WHAT TO DO.
- ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS REACH OUT.
- UH, SAKAI?
- HUH?
IS IT ALL RIGHT
IF I WAIT FOR YOU?
- WHAT?
- WELL, I MEAN,
UNTIL YOU MAKE A DECISION.
MAYBE IT'S SELFISH OF ME,
BUT I CAN'T GIVE UP
ON THE IDEA OF US.
I WANNA KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE WITH YOU.
I WANT YOU TO LOVE ME
THE WAY I LOVE YOU.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T WANNA GIVE UP
TILL YOU'VE MADE A DECISION.
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU.
- YEAH, THAT'S OKAY.
- Boy:
TESTING, ONE, TWO.
HELLO FROM
THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL COMMITTEE.
AND NOW WITHOUT FURTHER ADO,
ANNOUNCING THE GRAND PRIZE
FINALISTS.
- ( cheering )
- FROM CLASS ONE,
SHO-TARO KAWAKAMI.
AND FROM CLASS TWO, YUJI SAKAI,
YUKARI HIRAI
AND KAZUMI YOSHIDA.
- THEY PICKED BOTH YUJI
AND THE MIDGET?
- LASTLY, FROM CLASS THREE,
TOSHIKO KURODA.
- Both: ALL RIGHT!
IF I CALLED YOUR NAME, PLEASE
CHANGE BACK INTO YOUR COSTUME
AND MAKE YOUR WAY TO THE STAGE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- YOUR SPEECH, YOU GET TO
SAY WHATEVER YOU WANT TO.
LIKE IF THERE'S SOMETHING YOU
WANNA SAY TO SAKAI FOR INSTANCE,
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE TO DO IT.
- THIS IS MY CHANCE
TO TELL HIM AGAIN, FOR REAL.
I LOVE HIM.
- OH, NO, I'M GONNA BE
THE LAST ONE UP THERE.
- WAIT, DON'T FORGET
YOUR HAIR BOWS.
- ( wind howling )
- THAT WIND.
- CAN'T BELIEVE SAKAI
COULD WIN THIS.
HE'S NO ROMEO.
- RIGHT?
I FIGURED YOSHIDA WOULD,
BUT SAKAI WAS A LONG SHOT.
- GIVE HIM A BREAK,
HE WAS A GREAT ROMEO.
NOT TO MENTION HE WAS THE ONLY
GUY WHO MADE IT THROUGH
THE WHOLE PARADE UNSCATHED
AND HE HAD IKE ON HIS SHOULDER
HALF THE WAY.
- THE MOMENT YOU'VE ALL BEEN
WAITING FOR.
FIRST UP, WE'LL ANNOUNCE
YOUR CHOICE
FOR THE BEST GIRL'S COSTUME.
OUR GRAND PRIZE WINNER IS
CUTE LITTLE DOROTHY
FROM THE WIZARD OF OZ.  SHANA!
A.K.A. YUKARI HIRAI.
- ( cheering )
- OKAY.
- ( laughing )
- All: YEAH!
- SHANA, WOULD YOU
PLEASE STEP FORWARD?
- WEIRD.  I'M NOT NERVOUS.
- WANNA SAY A FEW WORDS?
- YUJI!
- ( murmuring )
- I WANTED TO SAY...
- ( shouting )
- ( screaming )
- IT'S PHELES!
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE BUSY AUTUMN FESTIVAL
SCREECHES TO A HALT
WHEN PHELES ARRIVES
AND A SEAL IS CAST.
WILHELMINA TRIES TO STOP HER,
WHILE SHANA ATTEMPTS TO SAVE ME.
MARGERY GOES BERSERK WHEN SHE
CATCHES A GLIMPSE OF THE SILVER,
AND TANAKA WATCHES AS OGATA
DISAPPEARS INTO THE FLAMES.
NEXT TIME ON
"SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II"...
"CONVERGENCE, THEN AN OMEN."