- Announcer:
IN 20th CENTURY NEW YORK,
MARGERY MET A YOUNG FLAME HAZE
BY THE NAME OF YURI.
THOUGH HE FOLLOWED
THE FLAME HAZE MISSION,
HE WAS PREOCCUPIED
WITH SAVING HUMAN LIVES.
MARGERY HAD NO PATIENCE
FOR THE BOY'S NAIVETE.
SHE LEFT HIM BEHIND
AS SHE WENT IN SEARCH
OF THE CRIMSON DENIZEN ANNABERG.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Alastor:
LISTEN CLOSELY, YUJI SAKAI.
THROUGH YOUR TRAINING,
YOU HAVE LEARNED TO CONTROL
YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
ARE YOU READY TO MOVE ON TO
CASTING AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL?
- UH, SURE.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- WELL, DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I'M GLAD ALL OF MY HARD WORK
IS PAYING OFF
AND I'D LIKE TO THINK I'M READY
TO MOVE FORWARD,
BUT IT JUST MAKES ME NERVOUS.
I MEAN, WHAT IF I SCREW
EVERYTHING UP?
- YOU CAN DO IT.
I HAVE COMPLETE FAITH
IN YOU, YUJI.
- ( sighs )
- Margery:
CAST A SEAL!
- MARCOSIAS, THE CLAWS
AND FANGS OF VIOLATION.
AND MARGERY DAW,
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I'M HONORED YOU'RE HERE
TO OBSERVE MY WORK.
- I CAN TELL BY THAT COCKY
ATTITUDE OF YOURS
THAT YOU'RE NOT WORKING
ALONE.
CARE TO TELL US
WHO YOU BROUGHT WITH YOU?
- Marcosias: THE MORE
THE MERRIER, I ALWAYS SAY!
NOW LET'S GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD! ( laughs )
- Valac: THE BATTLE HAS BEGUN.
- YEAH.
- YOU NEVER SHOULD'VE
SHARED YOUR STORY...
NOT WITH
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
ALL THAT NONSENSE ABOUT
WANTING TO SAVE
PEOPLE'S LIVES.
IT'S NO WONDER SHE REJECTED
YOUR NAIVE VIEW
OF THE FLAME HAZE MISSION.
- YEAH. I FIGURED SHE WOULD.
I EXPECTED IT.
EVEN SO, IT WAS SOMETHING
THAT NEEDED TO BE SAID.
WHAT I WANT.  IT ISN'T WRONG.
- Tanaka: I GUESS I MUST'VE
MISSED SOMETHING
'CAUSE I DON'T SEE THE PROBLEM.
THIS YURI KID.
HE WANTED TO HELP PEOPLE,
RIGHT, TO SAVE LIVES?
HOW IS THAT WRONG?
- LET ME ASK YOU THIS,
IF YOU BOYS WERE FLAME HAZE
AND YOU KNEW MY LIFE
WAS IN DANGER,
BUT I HAD ORDERED YOU NOT
TO FOLLOW ME INTO BATTLE.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
- WE'D TRY TO SAVE YOU.
RIGHT, DUDE?
- PATHETIC.  HONESTLY.
I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
FLAME HAZE.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT'VE RETAINED
A SHRED OF THE HUMANITY
YOU ONCE POSSESSED.
IT SEEMS I WAS WRONG.
- YOU TALK TOO MUCH!
- Marcosias:
WE'RE SENDING YOU TO HELL!
- YOU'RE A SOULLESS CREATURE,
DRIVEN BY YOUR MURDEROUS RAGE.
- THERE'S SOMETHING ODD
ABOUT HIS PRESENCE.
- Marcosias: I FEEL IT TOO.
HE'S GOT A TRICK UP HIS SLEEVE.
I JUST CAN'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT IT IS.
- I SPECIALIZE
IN THE MANIPULATION OF STEAM
AND THE ART OF CONCEALMENT.
MY CLOUDS OF VAPOR CAN
HIDE ALMOST ANYTHING.
EVEN A PRESENCE.
- Margery:
I KNEW HE WAS UP TO SOMETHING.
- Marcosias:
TALK ABOUT A DIRTY TRICK.
- BUT A PRETTY FACE LIKE MINE
CAN'T STAY HIDDEN.
- IF YOU THINK YOU CAN
SURPRISE ME THAT EASILY,
YOU'RE IN FOR A WORLD OF HURT.
- Valac: IT'S NOT A MATTER
OF RIGHT OR WRONG.
- Yuri: HELPING THOSE IN NEED.
SAVING PEOPLE'S LIVES.
I HONESTLY BELIEVE
THAT IS MY DESTINY.
IT IS MY PURPOSE
AS A FLAME HAZE.
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES IS OUT
THERE FIGHTING FOR HER LIFE.
AND I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN HELP HER.
- YOUR PURPOSE IS HUNTING
CRIMSON DENIZENS,
NOT SAVING LIVES.
HELPING OTHERS IS
NOT YOUR OBJECTIVE.
IT'S MERELY A BY-PRODUCT.
HOWEVER, THIS PARTICULAR
SITUATION MAY LEND ITSELF
TO DOING THINGS YOUR WAY.
- REALLY, DO YOU MEAN IT, VALAC?
- YOU HAD BETTER HURRY
BEFORE I CHANGE MY MIND.
- PUNCH AND JUDY FOUGHT
FOR A PIE.
- PUNCH GAVE JUDY A BLOW
IN THE EYE.
- WHAT THE--?
- THAT'S NO STANDARD ELEGY.
- THANKS FOR MAKING OUR JOB
EASY, THOUSAND CHANGES.
- HE WAS EVEN NICE ENOUGH
TO DIG HIS OWN GRAVE.
( laughing )
- Annaberg: I WOULD
HAVE PREFERRED YOU HAD
DEMOLISHED THE BUILDING
WITHOUT YOUR SEAL IN PLACE.
- YOU WANTED IT
TO BE DESTROYED?
- NATURALLY.
IT'S ALL IN THE NAME
OF PROGRESS, MY DEAR.
I'M ACCELERATING CIVILIZATION.
ISN'T IT A WONDROUS THING
TO BEHOLD?
THESE BUILDINGS REPRESENT
THE POWER OF HUMANITY
AND ITS ABILITY
TO SHAPE THE WORLD.
WHEN HUMANITY FACES A LOSS,
THEIR GOAL IS TO REBUILD
BIGGER AND BETTER.
I WILL STRIKE THEM DOWN
TO HELP THEM GROW STRONGER.
IT'S MY JOB TO NUDGE THEM ALONG,
TO MOTIVATE THEM,
TO FORCE THEM INTO ACTION.
THEY ARE FUELED BY ADVERSITY
SO I WILL DESTROY
WHAT THEY HAVE WROUGHT.
WHEN I AM FINISHED...
THEY WILL RISE FROM THE ASHES
WITH RENEWED STRENGTH,
POSSESSING THE POWER
TO CHANGE THE WORLD
AND IT WILL BE MY DOING,
MY MASTERPIECE.
I WILL BE THE ARCHITECT
OF THEIR EVOLUTION.
- SOME SPEECH.
YOU BEEN PRACTICING THAT?
TOO BAD IT'S JUST THE EMPTY
RAMBLINGS OF A MANIAC.
- I WOULDN'T EXPECT AN EMPTY
CARAPACE THAT FORSOOK
ITS OWN HUMANITY
TO UNDERSTAND.
- HA HA!  YOU SURE ARE FULL
OF HOT AIR, AREN'T YOU?
SORRY, PAL.  IT'S BEEN FUN,
BUT THE PARTY'S OVER NOW.
BEHIND YOU!
- ( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- MARGERY!
- ( panting )
- Yuri:
CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- HMM.
- CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- GOOD RIDDANCE PEST.
- THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- Annaberg:
NEVER FEAR.
WE WILL STILL BE THE VICTORS.
- Margery:
THOUSAND CHANGES.
- Marcosias: HE'S TAKEN ON
TWO SEPARATE FORMS.
- Sydonay:
( laughs ) LET ME GUESS.
YOU THOUGHT I'D BE DISTRACTED
WITH PROTECTING MY CLIENT.
- I HAVE TO MOVE QUICKLY.
IF I DON'T DO SOMETHING
SOON, SHE'LL DIE.
- Valac: I'M AFRAID SO.  ARE
YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
- I AM.
- THEN CALL ON YOUR FAMILIARS
TO ENSHROUD YOU WITH POWER.
IT MAY NOT BE THE MOST
GRACEFUL ATTACK,
BUT IT'S A STRONG ONE.
IF YOU'RE EVER GOING TO USE IT,
THIS IS THE TIME.
- I WILL TAKE FLIGHT.
- YOU SWORE AN OATH.
- I WILL FIGHT THIS BATTLE.
- YOU HAVE CHOSEN A PATH.
- I'LL SAVE HER.  I SWEAR IT!
- Sydonay:
( laughs ) BEAUTIFUL FLOWER.
EVEN MORE CAPTIVATING
AS IT WITHERS AND DIES.
THIS ENDS NOW.
- ( gasps )
- ( grunting ) WHAT WAS--
- I COULDN'T LET YOU
DO THIS ALONE.
YOU'RE WOUNDED.
- IT'S GONNA TAKE A LOT MORE
THAN THAT TO KILL HIM.
BUT DON'T GIVE UP NOW.
JUST KEEP TRYING.
- I WILL.
- Marcosias:
THE ROOKIE SAVED YOUR LIFE?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
YOU TAKE MORE RISKS THAN
A TIGHTROPE WALKER,
MY DEAR MARGERY DAW.
- ( scoffs )
- Annaberg:
ANOTHER FLAME HAZE!
- I FOUND HIM.
- ( screams )
- DAMN IT!
MY CLIENT IS IN DANGER.
HUH?
- OVER HERE.  I'M YOUR OPPONENT.
- I'M IMPRESSED YOU'RE
STILL ABLE TO FIGHT
AFTER THAT HIT YOU TOOK.
- YOU JUST SPOKE
YOUR LAST WORDS.
( roars )
- I COULDN'T FINISH IT.
- YOU'RE DOING WELL
FOR YOUR FIRST BATTLE.
BUT BE CAREFUL.  YOU'RE
EXPENDING TOO MUCH ENERGY.
YOU CAN'T KEEP THIS UP.
- YEAH, I KNOW, BUT...
THIS IS SUCH
AN AMAZING POWER.
JUST THINK HOW MANY PEOPLE
I COULD SAVE USING THIS.
- ( crash )
- DAMN YOU.
MEDDLING FLAME HAZE!
- Valac: THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
TAKE HIM DOWN.
- YEAH.
- ( grunting )
- I GOT HIM.
- Valac: NOT YET.
HE'S FEEDING OFF YOUR POWER.
YOU NEED TO SHAKE HIM.
- IMPOSSIBLE!
I CANNOT BE KILLED
BY A FLAME HAZE.
I'VE BEEN DEFEATED
BY THE HOLLOW SHELL
OF A HUMAN.
- I'M NOT LIKE
THE OTHER FLAME HAZE.
I'M NOT.  I'M MORE.
I HAVE A HIGHER PURPOSE!
I FIGHT TO SAVE LIVES.
- Tanaka:
AWESOME!  THAT KID'S BADASS.
SO WHAT HAPPENED NEXT?
COME ON, SPILL.
I BET YOU AND YURI UNLEASHED
A WORLD OF PAIN
ON THAT SHAPE SHIFTING
SYDONAY JERK, DIDN'T YOU?
- Valac: DON'T BE RECKLESS.
LET THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
HANDLE THOUSAND CHANGES.
- Yuri: I CAN'T.
SHE'S BEEN BADLY INJURED.
- YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY AT THE
HEIGHT OF YOUR POWER, EITHER.
- I KNOW.  STILL, I HAVE TO
DO SOMETHING TO HELP HER.
- THIS DESIRE TO SAVE OTHERS.
YOU JUST CAN'T LET IT GO,
CAN YOU?
- THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
A CLIENT HAS EVER DIED
ON MY WATCH.
YOU'VE HUMILIATED ME.
- YOU WON'T HAVE TO FEEL
THAT WAY FOR LONG.
SOON YOU TOO WILL BE DEAD.
THAT SHOULD OFFER SOME RELIEF.
- I'VE HEARD RUMOR
OF HER INSATIABLE BLOODLUST.
WITH THE DEATH OF THE CHASM
OF FASTIDIOUS IMPALING,
THERE'S NO REASON
TO CONTINUE FIGHTING.
- ( panting )
YURI.
- HE'S BACK.
HMM, PERFECT TIMING.
I'LL LET HIS APPEARANCE
PUT AN END TO THIS BATTLE.
- HOW MUCH IS THE KID WILLING
TO GAMBLE?
- Marcosias: SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
IF WE HIT HIM FROM BOTH SIDES,
WE MIGHT HAVE A SLIM CHANCE
OF BEATING HIM.
- NO, I CAN'T RISK MY LIFE.
NOT UNTIL I HAVE MY REVENGE.
I SHOULD'VE BEEN THE ONE.
IT SHOULD'VE BEEN MY HANDS
THAT WERE STAINED
WITH THEIR BLOOD, NOT HIS.
I STILL HEAR IT.
I CAN STILL HEAR HIS LAUGHTER.
I REMEMBER THE JOY HE TOOK
IN MOCKING MY PAIN.
I WON'T RISK MY LIFE
IN THIS MEANINGLESS BATTLE.
I CANNOT DIE
UNTIL I'VE HAD MY REVENGE.
CHANTER OF ELEG--
I'M SORRY, VALAC.
- YOU GOT YOUR WISH,
DIDN'T YOU?
- Marcosias: IF THE ROOKIE
HADN'T JUMPED IN WHEN HE DID,
THEY WOULD'VE KEPT FIGHTING
UNTIL ONE OF 'EM WOUND UP DEAD,
BUT THE BATTLE ENDED IN A DRAW
AND TWO LIVES WERE SAVED.
THANKS TO HIM.
- Margery: HE DIDN'T HESITATE
FOR A MOMENT.
UNFORTUNATELY, NEITHER DID I.
- Tanaka: I GUESS SHE DOESN'T
WANT US TO FOLLOW HER.
WHY ELSE WOULD SHE
TELL THAT STORY?
MAN, I NEVER KNEW SHE
HAD SUCH A ROUGH PAST.
SHE HAD THE CHANCE TO TAKE
REVENGE AGAINST HER ENEMIES.
BUT THE SILVER GOT
TO THEM FIRST.
NOW SHE'S HUNTING HIM DOWN.
NO WONDER SHE TURNED OUT
AS STRONG AS SHE IS.
SERIOUSLY,
SHE'S TOUGH AS NAILS.
- WERE YOU EVEN
PAYING ATTENTION?
- ( panting )
THERE'S JUST NO WAY.
I DON'T THINK I CAN DO IT.
- Alastor: COMPLAINING WILL
GET YOU NOWHERE.
CASTING AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL
TAKES PRACTICE.
IT IS NOT SOMETHING THAT CAN BE
TAUGHT.
YOU MUST MASTER IT YOURSELF.
- DON'T GIVE UP NOW.
YOU CAN CONTROL
THE POWER INSIDE YOU.
- YOU THINK?
CAST A SEAL.
- OH, WOW.
I DID IT, SHANA.
SOMETHING WRONG?
- Alastor: THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
HIS FLAME.
LOOK AT THE COLOR.
- SILVER.
- Margery: ONE DAY
I WILL HAVE MY REVENGE.
I WILL SACRIFICE ANYTHING
TO SEE HIM DEAD BY MY HAND.
NOTHING IS MORE IMPORTANT TO ME.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: MISAKI HIGH SCHOOL'S
ANNUAL AUTUMN FESTIVAL
IS FAST APPROACHING.
YOSHIDA AND SHANA ARE CHOSEN
FOR IMPORTANT ROLES
IN THE COSTUME PARADE.
THEY VISIT MY MOM
FOR COSTUME MATERIALS
AND SOME WOMANLY ADVICE.
ON THEIR WAY HOME, THEY
ENCOUNTER A SUSPICIOUS STRANGER.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT MAN LOOKS FAMILIAR.
NEXT TIME ON
"SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND"--
"THE MAN WHO RETURNED."