- ( Alastor's voice )
A STUDY SESSION AT SATO'S HOUSE
BECAME AN OPPORTUNITY
FOR A LIFE LESSON
WHEN MARGERY OFFERED
WORDS OF WISDOM TO THE GIRLS.
SHANA AND KAZUMI
HAD BEEN UNEASY
EVER SINCE FUMINA KONOE
TRANSFERRED TO THEIR SCHOOL.
BUT MARGERY'S ADVICE
HELPED THEM SET ASIDE
THEIR JEALOUSY OF THE NEW GIRL
AND OF ONE ANOTHER.
- ( upbeat song playing )
- DEPARTURE TIME--
CHECK.
DIRECTIONS TO DESTINATION--
A DESCRIPTION OF EVERY RIDE,
INCLUDING ITS LOCATION
AND RELEVANT WARNINGS--
CHECK.
THE LOCATIONS OF
AND DIRECTIONS TO
THE FOOD COURT
AND BATHROOMS-- CHECK.
AND NOW THE FINAL
VARIABLE--
THE WEATHER TOMORROW
FOR MISAKI AND OUTO.
CHECK.
THIS IS PERFECT.
EVERYTHING'S READY.
I'VE PLANNED FOR
EVERY CONTINGENCY.
NO MATTER
WHAT HAPPENS TOMORROW,
KONOE AND THE REST OF THE GANG
WILL HAVE AN AWESOME TIME.
HOPEFULLY, EVERYTHING GOES
ACCORDING TO PLAN.
'CAUSE THEN
I'LL RIDE THE FERRIS WHEEL
WITH YOSHIDA AT MY SIDE.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE EVERYONE'S HERE.
GLAD TO SEE
NONE OF YOU WERE LATE.
- WHO WOULD HAVE DARED?
YOU DIDN'T LEAVE MUCH ROOM
TO DEVIATE FROM THE PLAN.
YOU TOLD US
WHICH BUS TO TAKE
AND THE EXACT TIME
THE TRAIN WOULD BE LEAVING.
AND YOU CALLED AGAIN YESTERDAY,
JUST TO REMIND US.
- YEAH, NOTHING LIKE
AN EARLY MORNING WAKE-UP CALL.
IF WE HAD BEEN LATE,
YOU WOULD HAVE FREAKED.
- HE CALLED YOU?
- YEAH, BUT WILHELMINA
ANSWERED THE PHONE.
- Hayato: Yeah, we'll all
buy our tickets
at the entrance gate
when we get there.
- HOW MUCH TIME
WILL THAT REQUIRE?
- Two to three minutes.
- HE DIDN'T GIVE ME
ANY DETAILED PLAN LIKE THAT.
- I'M BETTING THAT'S BECAUSE HE
KNOWS YOU'RE THE MOST ORGANIZED.
- WE SHOULDN'T HARP ON HIM
JUST FOR BEING PREPARED.
ALL THAT REALLY MATTERS
IS WE'RE HERE NOW.
TODAY'S AN IMPORTANT DAY.
IT'S KONOE'S FIRST TIME
AT AN AMUSEMENT PARK.
IT NEEDS
TO BE AWESOME.
THAT WAY SHE'LL REMEMBER
HOW MUCH FUN SHE HAD.
- NO WORRIES.
I HAVE A LIST OF THINGS
FOR US TO DO.
IF YOU FAIL TO PLAN,
THEN YOU ARE PLANNING TO FAIL.
I'VE ALWAYS LIKED
THAT SAYING.
- MAN, YOU'RE SO SMART.
- HE JUST LOOKS SMART
'CAUSE OF THOSE GLASSES.
- YAY, HERE'S TO THE
SMARTEST-LOOKING GUY IN TOWN.
- ( all laugh )
- PLEASE.
IT WAS NOTHING.
- ALL RIGHT,
I GOT YOSHIDA'S ATTENTION--
ONE MORE THING
ACCOMPLISHED.
NOW TO SHOW HER
WHAT A RELIABLE LEADER I AM.
THAT'S SURE
TO IMPRESS HER.
- OKAY, IT'S TIME
TO GET STARTED.
EVERYONE FOLLOW ME
INTO THE PARK.
- LEAD ON, IKE.
WHICH RIDE
ARE WE GOING ON FIRST?
THE HAUNTED MANOR?
THE AFRICAN SAFARI BOAT?
OR SHOULD WE JUMP
RIGHT TO THE COASTERS?
- NOW WE DON'T WANT
TO SCARE KONOE.
WE'LL SAVE THAT
FOR LATER.
I KNOW-- LET'S GIVE HER
A TOUR OF THE PARK FIRST.
WHAT BETTER WAY
TO SOAK UP THE ATMOSPHERE?
LET'S NOT FORGET,
TODAY'S ALL ABOUT HER.
WE HAVE TO TREAT HER
LIKE OUR HONORED GUEST.
I MADE SURE WE COULD
TAKE OUR TIME TODAY.
I WANT HER TO ENJOY
EVERY MINUTE OF IT.
- SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
- YEAH, GOOD THINKING.
- I'VE TAKEN A LOOK
AT THE PARK MAP
AND DETERMINED THE PERFECT ROUTE
FOR US TO FOLLOW.
FIRST, WE'LL TAKE A STROLL
PAST THE MAIN ATTRACTIONS.
I'VE SELECTED
AN EXCELLENT PATH.
IT'S FAST
AND THE SCENERY IS--
- Eita: HEY,
WHERE'D KONOE GO?
- KONOE, DO YOU WANT TO GO
ON THIS RIDE?
- YEAH, IT LOOKS LIKE
A LOT OF FUN.
- I THINK THAT ONE'S MEANT
FOR LITTLE KIDS.
- WELL, IKE?
- NO PROBLEM.
I DIDN'T INCLUDE THIS RIDE
IN MY INITIAL PLANS,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
WE HAVE TO SKIP IT EITHER.
GO ON, KONOE.
WE CAME HERE TODAY
TO SHOW YOU A GOOD TIME.
YOU CAN RIDE
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- WELL, IN THAT CASE...
- THIS IS HUMILIATING.
WHY DO WE HAVE TO RIDE IT TOO?
- BE A GOOD SPORT.
THIS IS WHAT KONOE WANTED.
- IT'S MORE FUN
IF EVERYBODY RIDES TOGETHER.
- UH, YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- HOW EMBARRASSING.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I NEVER PREDICTED KONOE WOULD
WANT TO DO SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
THE DAY'S JUST STARTED AND I'VE
ALREADY MADE A MAJOR MISTAKE.
- UM, IKE,
AREN'T YOU WORRIED
RIDING SOMETHING LIKE THIS
WILL MAKE YOU MOTION-SICK?
- NO.
I THINK I SHOULD BE OKAY.
- Woman: EVERYONE READY?
- Kids: YEAH.
- LET'S GO!
- I THOUGHT
THIS MIGHT HAPPEN.
YOU OKAY?
- YEAH.
- WE HAVE NO CHANCE
OF SCORING, EVER.
- YEAH, RIGHT?  DO WE HAVE
TO TURN IN OUR MAN CARDS?
- I SHOULDN'T HAVE
UNDERESTIMATED THAT RIDE
JUST BECAUSE
IT'S FOR KIDS.
WHAT GOOD AM I
AS A LEADER
IF I CAN'T TELL WHICH RIDES
ARE TOO DANGEROUS TO GO ON?
- LET'S TRY
THAT ONE OVER THERE.
- IKE.
- UH, WE'VE GOT AN IDEA.
- A GOOD ONE.
- IT'S NOT THAT I MIND
SPLITTING UP INTO TWO GROUPS.
IT'S JUST WEIRD.
I ALWAYS SEEM TO END UP
WITH YOU GUYS.
AT LEAST SHANA'S WITH ME.
- WELL, WE DREW NAMES.
IT MUST BE FATE.
- I THINK
IT'S FOR THE BEST.
KONOE'S BETTER OFF WITH IKE,
SINCE HE'S THE ORGANIZER.
- TRUE.  AND WE'LL MEET BACK UP
WITH THEM AT LUNCH.
OKAY, SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS
WANT TO DO UNTIL THEN?
HEY, SHANA.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO RIDE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
HEY LET'S GO
ON THAT.
- THE BUNGEE?
- THE GREAT THING
ABOUT THIS AMUSEMENT PARK
IS THEY OFFER A VARIETY
OF SWEET TREATS.
SPEAKING OF,
THERE'S AN AMAZING CHEESECAKE
SHOP HERE WE SHOULD TRY.
UH, HOW ABOUT ICE CREAM?
THERE'S STILL
THE JAPANESE SWEET SHOP.
NO WAY.
I KNOW I SAW IT.
BUT I CAN'T FIND IT
ON THE MAP.
- EH, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
- I'M REAL SORRY.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH ME TODAY.
TOO MANY MISTAKES
AND NOT ENOUGH RESEARCH.
I WAS LUCKY ENOUGH
TO BE GROUPED WITH YOSHIDA,
BUT I'M MAKING
A TOTAL MESS OF IT.
- I KNOW
IT LOOKS SCARY,
BUT ROLLERCOASTERS ARE
ACTUALLY A WHOLE LOT OF FUN.
- A ROLLERCOASTER?  HUH.
WELL, I'LL GO ON IT
IF YOU RIDE BESIDE ME.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DO IT.
- WELL, ACCORDING TO
MY RESEARCH,
THIS PARTICULAR COASTER
TENDS TO BE LESS CROWDED
IN THE MORNING
THAN IN THE AFTERNOON.
SO NOW'S OUR CHANCE.
LET'S GO.
NO!  THE LINE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE SHORTER THAN THIS.
IMPOSSIBLE!
- HECK OF A LINE.
- IS THIS WHAT THEY CONSIDER
LESS CROWDED?
- Yuji: IT'S RARE FOR IKE
TO MISJUDGE LIKE THIS.
- Kazumi: HE'S USUALLY
SO ACCURATE ABOUT EVERYTHING.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
I GATHERED ANY DATA THAT WAS
EVEN REMOTELY RELEVANT
AND ANALYZED IT
MULTIPLE TIMES.
WHERE COULD I HAVE
GONE WRONG?
IT'S A LOST CAUSE.
I'VE MADE SUCH A FOOL OF MYSELF.
I CAN'T POSSIBLY
ASK YOSHIDA
TO RIDE THE FERRIS WHEEL
WITH ME NOW.
I HAVE TO THINK.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
I CAN DO TO SAVE FACE.
- IT'S UP TO YOU, KONOE.
WE CAN WAIT IN THAT LONG LINE
OR WE CAN TRY AGAIN LATER.
- WELL, I'M NOT SURE.
- DON'T GIVE UP, YOU GUYS.
IT'S ALL GOOD.  I GOT THIS.
I'LL WAIT IN LINE
AND YOU CAN GO ENJOY
ALL THAT THE PARK HAS TO OFFER.
- ( Hayato's voice )
WELL, I TRIED TO PLAY THE HERO,
BUT IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE
YOSHIDA WAS ESPECIALLY TOUCHED
BY MY GRAND GESTURE.
I GUESS
IT WAS WORTH A TRY.
BUT I'VE MADE
SO MANY MISTAKES TODAY,
I SHOULDN'T EXPECT
TO MAKE UP FOR IT THAT EASILY.
( sighs )
I BET THE OTHERS
ARE HAVING FUN.
I SPENT SO MANY DAYS
RESEARCHING THIS.
I STAYED UP
NIGHT AFTER NIGHT,
TRYING TO MAKE SURE
IT WAS PERFECT.
AND THIS IS
THE RESULT I GET?
I THINK IT'S TIME
TO GIVE UP.
YOSHIDA WILL NEVER WANT TO RIDE
THE FERRIS WHEEL WITH ME
AFTER HOW MUCH
I'VE SCREWED UP.
IT WOULD BE POINTLESS
TO ASK.
I TOOK ON
MORE THAN I COULD HANDLE.
BIG PLANS
MEAN BIG FAILURES.
- THANK YOU.
- I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT BE LONELY,
WAITING HERE BY YOURSELF.
SAKAI'S OFF
LOOKING AFTER KONOE.
- OH, THAT'S COOL.
- IKE, DON'T
STRESS YOURSELF OUT.
YOU'RE NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR EVERYONE ELSE'S GOOD TIME.
- OH, YOSHIDA,
YOU'RE SO KIND TO ME,
WHEN I'VE DONE NOTHING
BUT MAKE MISTAKES.
- Kazumi: YEAH, SO...
DO YOU GET MOTION-SICK
ON ROLLERCOASTERS TOO?
- YEAH, I DO,
PRETTY BAD.
BUT I FIGURED YOU GUYS
COULD GO WITHOUT ME.
I'LL JUST WAIT
AT THE EXIT.
- OH.
SO ARE THERE ANY RIDES HERE
THAT DON'T MAKE YOU SICK?
- WELL, THE FERRIS WHEEL'S
FINE.
- THE FERRIS WHEEL?
- MM-HMM.
I WENT ON ONE
BACK IN KINDERGARTEN,
AND IT WAS THE ONE RIDE
I WAS OKAY ON.
EVERYTHING ELSE
IS JUST TOO FAST, SO...
SO I WAS WONDERING--
IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND,
I THOUGHT MAYBE
AFTER YOU GUYS GET OFF
THE ROLLERCOASTER WITH KONOE--
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU'D RIDE
ON THE FERRIS WHEEL WITH ME.
- UM, SURE.
- ( people screaming )
- SO MANY THRILL RIDES.
NEED A SEC.
- FOR REAL.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU GUYS,
BUT MY BACK'S KILLING ME.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN WALK.
- REALLY?
- Matake: YOU'RE SOMETHING,
SHANA.
YOU DON'T FLINCH AT ANY RIDE,
NO MATTER HOW SCARY IT IS.
YOU'RE LIKE A SUPERHERO.
- YEAH.
- I SEE NO REASON
TO BE AFRAID.
EACH RIDE'S SPEED
AND CENTRIPETAL FORCE
ARE SET FOR HARMLESS
ENTERTAINMENT.
AND THEY EXPECT IT
TO BE SCARY?
- HEY, I'LL GO GET THE OTHERS
AND BRING THEM HERE.
- THAT'LL WORK.  TELL THEM
IT'S MOVING PRETTY FAST NOW.
- OKAY.
- ACCORDING TO
MY CALCULATIONS,
THIS COASTER HAS A 32-PERSON
CAPACITY PER RUN.
SO OUR TURN SHOULD COME
IN THREE OR FOUR ROUNDS.
THEY SHOULD MAKE IT
JUST IN TIME.
WAIT.  OH, NO.
WHAT IF THEY
DON'T MAKE IT?
THEN I'LL HAVE
TO RIDE.
- ( people screaming )
- I DON'T HAVE LUCK
WITH COASTERS.
THAT ONE TIME,
I GOT SO SICK AFTERWARDS,
I HAD TO SKIP SCHOOL
THE NEXT DAY.
AND THAT OTHER TIME, THEY HAD
TO CART ME OFF IN AN AMBULANCE.
NO, I HAVE TO STAY CALM.
IF I LEAVE THE LINE NOW, KONOE
WILL MISS HER CHANCE TO RIDE IT.
WORSE, YOSHIDA
MIGHT DECIDE
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO RIDE THE
FERRIS WHEEL WITH ME AFTER ALL.
IT'S OKAY.
SHE'LL FIND THEM
AND THEY'LL MAKE IT BACK
IN TIME.  THEY WILL.
THEY HAVE TO.
- EXCUSE ME.
COMING THROUGH.
THE GROUP UP AT THE FRONT
DECIDED NOT TO RIDE,
SO THE LINE'S
MOVED UP A BIT.
EVERYONE IN FRONT OF THE ROPE
GOES NEXT.
- HUH?
- ( people screaming )
- THAT'S STRANGE.
THAT SCREAM SOUNDED
JUST LIKE IKE.
- YOSHIDA, ARE WE
ALMOST UP IN LINE?
- YEAH, WE SHOULD START
HEADING OVER THERE.
- I'M SORRY WE MISSED IT.
- DON'T BE.
I DIDN'T THINK THE LINE
WOULD MOVE SO FA--
( hiccups )
- POOR GUY.
- I'M SO SORRY, KONOE.
I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU WANTED
TO RIDE THE ROLLERCOASTER.
- YEAH,
SO ABOUT THAT, IKE:
THE LINE'S DOWN TO, LIKE,
NOTHING RIGHT NOW.
-  ( screaming )
- I SEE.  THE NEW MAGIC SHOW
IS ABOUT TO START.
THAT'S WHY THE LINE
FOR THE COASTER
IS SO SHORT
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
ALL RIGHT, I QUIT.
I RELINQUISH MY DREAM.
GOODBYE, FERRIS WHEEL RIDE
WITH YOSHIDA.
- WOW, WHAT A GLORIOUS DAY.
- WOW, SHE'S AMAZING!
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
YOU GOT THE HIGHEST SCORE
IN THE PARK'S HISTORY.
YOU WON A PRIZE!
- UH, THANKS.
- AWESOME.
THAT WAS SOME SHOW.
YOU ROCKED IT,
SERIOUSLY.
MAN, YOU REALLY ARE
LIKE A SUPERHERO.
- Alastor: BE CAREFUL.
YOU SHOULD NOT
EXPEND YOUR STRENGTH
WITHOUT GOOD CAUSE.
- IF I WERE HER, I'D USE THAT
STRENGTH TO MY ADVANTAGE.
- MM-HMM.
- OH?
I'M TELLING YOU,
IT WAS INSANE.
SHE TOTALLY SLASHED 'EM ALL
AND WON A PRIZE.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
- WOW, I WISH
I COULD HAVE SEEN THAT.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?  SERIOUSLY,
IT WAS FREAKING AMAZING.
I COULDN'T WAIT
TO TELL YOU GUYS.
- UH, SHANA.
- CHILL OUT.  I WAS HAVING FUN.
- HEY, WHAT'S WITH HIM?
DID I MISS SOMETHING?
- I GUESS HE'S WALLOWING
IN SELF-LOATHING
'CAUSE HIS PLANS
FELL APART.
- HE'S NOT USED
TO FAILING.
- Fumina: UM, IKE?
I BROUGHT A BAG OF HOMEMADE
COOKIES FOR EVERYBODY.
I HOPE THEY'RE NOT
TOO SMOOSHED.
THINK THIS MIGHT
CHEER YOU UP?
- DELICIOUS.
- FOR YOU AND YOU.
- YES.  SHE HASN'T
FORSAKEN ME AFTER ALL.
SHE GAVE ME
MY COOKIES FIRST.
SHE MUST THINK
I'M SPECIAL.
THAT'S IT, I'M GONNA TRY THIS
ONE MORE TIME.
- GUYS, I'D LIKE TO ANNOUNCE
THE AFTERNOON PLAN.
IN FOUR GROUPS OF TWO,
WE'RE GONNA RACE EACH OTHER
THROUGH THE GIANT MAZE.
- THE RULES ARE SIMPLE.
THE PAIR THAT REACHES THE EXIT
FIRST IS THE WINNER.
THE PRIZE IS A SOFT-SERVE ICE
CREAM BOUGHT BY ALL THE LOSERS.
- HOW'D HE GO FROM DEPRESSED
TO MOTIVATED ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- WHO KNOWS?
- WHO CARES?
LET'S FOCUS ON WHAT MATTERS--
FREE ICE CREAM.
- LET'S SHOW 'EM HOW IT'S DONE.
- YEAH.
- OKAY.
READY?  BEGIN!
- I HAVE A FEELING
YOUR ANALYTICAL THINKING
IS GONNA
COME IN HANDY.
IN FACT, IT MIGHT GIVE US
A LEG UP ON THE OTHER TEAMS.
- "MIGHT" ISN'T
GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME.
- OH.
- WE'RE GONNA
WIN THIS RACE OR ELSE.
- HE'S SO SERIOUS.
MUST BE A BIG FAN
OF SOFT SERVE ICE CREAM.
- I HAVEN'T SEEN A GIANT MAZE
LIKE THIS IN A WHILE.
- WELL, THIS IS AN OLDER
AMUSEMENT PARK.
BUT I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY
GONE THROUGH HERE.
- I'M NO GOOD
AT THIS SORT OF THING.
- UH, GUESS NOT.
- Keisaku: HEY, CAN I
ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- WHAT?
- COULD I DO IT TOO?
BECOME A FLAME HAZE,
I MEAN.
- Alastor: WHY WOULD YOU
ASK SUCH A THING?
- WELL, I--
- OKAY, WHICH WAY
DO WE GO NOW?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- MAYBE THIS WAY?
OR...
- SO GO THAT WAY?
THANK YOU.
- WE APPRECIATE IT, SIR.
- WEIRDEST THEME PARK EVER.
- WOW, IKE, YOU HAVEN'T
GOTTEN US LOST ONCE.
- IF WE GET LOST,
WE CAN'T WIN.
AND LOSING TO THE OTHERS
IS NOT AN OPTION.
- ( Hayato's voice )
IT'S NOT LIKE I KNOW THE ROUTE
OR ANYTHING.
I CAN JUST SENSE IT.
MY INTUITION'S LEADING ME
TOWARDS THE EXIT.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE,
I CAN FEEL IT.
I'M PUTTING EVERYTHING I HAVE
INTO THIS ONE MOMENT.
- YOSHIDA, I ASKED YOU
SOMETHING
WHILE WE WERE IN LINE
FOR THE COASTER.
DO YOU REMEMBER?
- RIDING THE FERRIS WHEEL?
- IF WE'RE ABLE
TO WIN THIS RACE
AND GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE THE OTHERS,
TO CELEBRATE
OUR VICTORY,
I'D STILL LIKE YOU TO RIDE
THE FERRIS WHEEL WITH ME.
- IT'S ALMOST OUR TURN.
- YEAH.
- ( Hayato's voice )
I'M GLAD I DIDN'T GIVE UP.
SURE, I MADE A FEW
PLANNING MISTAKES,
BUT IF I CAN GO ON THIS RIDE
WITH YOSHIDA,
IT WON'T MATTER ANYMORE.
IT'S ALMOST TIME.
THIS WILL BE A MEMORY
ONLY THE TWO OF US WILL SHARE.
IF I'M REALLY LUCKY,
THIS SPECIAL MOMENT
MIGHT BE THE FIRST
OF MANY
THAT WE'LL SHARE TOGETHER
FOR THE REST OF OUR YEARS.
- ( Hayato retching )
- Kazumi: IKE, IKE!
OH GOSH, HANG ON.
- I'M SORRY.
- HE THOUGHT
THE FERRIS WHEEL
WOULDN'T BE
A MOTION SICKNESS ISSUE,
BUT HE GOT ALL QUEASY
HALFWAY THROUGH.
- Hayato: I SWEAR, WHEN I
RODE IT BACK IN KINDERGARTEN,
IT DIDN'T AFFECT ME
AT ALL.
- Yuji: MAYBE IT'S GETTING WORSE
AS YOU GET OLDER.
- MAYBE.
( gagging )
- ( Hayato's voice ) ALL DAY,
RIGHT TO THE VERY END,
I'VE MADE A FOOL OF MYSELF
IN FRONT OF YOSHIDA.
I WAS A CRAPPY
ORGANIZER.
I GOT ALL DEPRESSED
AND PATHETIC.
AND THEN I THREW UP
ON THE FERRIS WHEEL.
I CAN'T DO
ANYTHING RIGHT.
- WHAT IS IT, KONOE?
- IKE, YOU'RE THE BEST
ORGANIZER.
I HAD SO MUCH FUN TODAY.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE THE GREATEST.
- YOU DID A GOOD JOB.
SURE, SOME THINGS WENT WRONG,
BUT ALL THAT MATTERS IS
KONOE HAD A GOOD TIME.
- Keisaku: WE ABOUT
READY TO GO?
- Eita: THEY'RE GONNA
LOCK US IN.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
FANCY PARK DOESN'T CLOSE
ITS GATES THAT QUICKLY.
THEY WAIT AN HOUR
AFTER EVERYTHING SHUTS DOWN.
- Masake: YAY!  THAT'S THE IKE
WE KNOW AND LOVE.
- ( all laughing )
- ( Hayato's voice )
ALL'S WELL THAT ENDS WELL.
I'LL HAVE TO ADD THAT ONE
TO MY LIST OF FAVORITE SAYINGS.
- ( upbeat song playing )
- ( Yuji's voice )
MARGERY DAW,
ALSO KNOWN AS
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES--
SHE IS A POWERFUL AND
EXPERIENCED FLAME HAZE.
HER UNDERLINGS, SATO AND TANAKA,
PLEAD WITH HER TO TRAIN THEM.
THE YOUNG MEN'S REQUEST
AWAKENS
REPRESSED MEMORIES
OF MARGERY'S PAST--
MEMORIES OF NEW YORK
IN THE EARLY TWENTIETH CENTURY.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"THE DOOR TO THE PAST."