- Alastor: MARGERY RECOUNTED
THE STORY OF HER MEETING
WITH AN IDEALISTIC YOUNG FLAME
HAZE NAMED YURI.
DESPITE THEIR DIFFERENCES,
THE BOY SAVED HER LIFE
AFTER SHE WAS WOUNDED
IN BATTLE.
AS SUCH, TANAKA AND SATO
ARE SHOCKED TO HEAR HOW READILY
MARGERY SACRIFICED YURI'S LIFE
IN ORDER TO SAVE HER OWN.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( gasps )
- WHAT?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- YUJI.  YOUR FLAME'S COLOR.
- YEAH?
IT'S SILVER.
- Lamies:
DON'T CHASE THE SILVER.
- Marcosias: WHAT?
HOW DO YOU KNOW ABOUT HIM?
- Lamies: IT'S POINTLESS.
YOU'LL NEVER CATCH HIM.
YOU CAN SEARCH,
BUT YOU'LL NEVER FIND HIM.
HE SIMPLY APPEARS.
- I CAN'T GIVE UP.
I NEED MY REVENGE.
DO YOU THINK I CAN
JUST LET IT GO?
I CAN'T.  KILLING HIM IS
ALL THAT MATTERS TO ME.
- THAT GUY MARGERY
WAS HUNTING.
- SHE'S STILL SEARCHING.
- HIS FLAME.
WAS IT SILVER LIKE THIS?
- Alastor: YES, IT WAS.
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES IS STILL
HAUNTED BY THE SIGHT OF IT.
- IS IT A COMMON COLOR?
- NO, ONLY THE SILVER POSSESSES
A FLAME LIKE THIS.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK IT MEANS?
- I'M AFRAID I DON'T KNOW.
- Lamies: AS FAR AS I'M
CONCERNED, THIS HAS NO BEARING
ON WHO YOU ARE, YUJI SAKAI.
WE'LL ASK THE SPECIALIST
OF EVERYTHING ABOUT IT
WHEN SHE RETURNS.
- RIGHT.
LISTEN, PLEASE TRY NOT TO USE
YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
WE'LL HAVE TO PUT YOUR TRAINING
ON HOLD FOR NOW.
- AGREED. THIS MUST
BE KEPT SECRET FROM
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- YEAH, OKAY.
A TORCH.  A MYSTES.
AND NOW THE SILVER.
- Chigusa: HURRY UP, YUJI.
YOU'RE GONNA BE LATE.
- YEAH, OKAY.  LATER.
- HAVE A GOOD DAY.
SEE YOU TONIGHT.
- GOOD MORNING.
- MORNING.
I'M SORRY IF I'M LATE.
- NAH.
I GOT HERE KIND OF EARLY.
- IS SHE ON HER WAY?
- NO, KONOE'S NOT FEELING
TOO HOT.
HER BUTLER TOLD ME
SHE'LL STILL BE AT SCHOOL.
BUT HE'S GONNA DRIVE HER
BACK AND FORTH UNTIL
SHE'S FEELING BETTER.
- I HOPE SHE'S OKAY.
- Ike: LISTEN UP, EVERYBODY.
I GOT OUR ASSIGNMENTS
FROM THE COMMITTEE.
HERE'S WHAT WE'RE DOING
AT THE FESTIVAL.
I DON'T THINK IT
SHOULD BE TOO HARD.
OKAY, SO HERE'S THE DEAL.
WE'VE STILL GOT SOME RESEARCH
TO DO AND CONCESSIONS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
FORTUNATELY,
IT'S A FAIRLY SIMPLE THEME,
SO WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO
GET A GOOD AMOUNT DONE
WITHIN THE WEEK.
WE'LL HAVE TO ASK
THE UPPERCLASSMEN FOR TIPS
ON HOW TO RUN THE CREPE STAND.
THERE ARE A FEW THINGS WE
NEED TO DECIDE, THOUGH.
- ( all gasp )
- HEY, SHE MADE IT.
- I DO APOLOGIZE
FOR OUR TARDINESS.
AS ALWAYS, I TRUST SHE'S
IN GOOD HANDS WITH YOU.
- FEELING BETTER?
WE HEARD YOU'VE BEEN SICK.
- OH, I'M FINE NOW.
I'M SORRY IF MY BUTLER HAD
YOU ALL WORRIED ABOUT ME.
- SO GLAD YOU COULD JOIN US.
AND YOU MADE IT JUST IN TIME
TO HEAR ALL ABOUT
THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL.
- THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL?
- I GUESS IT'S NEW TO YOU, HUH?
- WELL, IKE.
YOU GONNA EXPLAIN IT TO HER?
- IT IS PRETTY SELF-EXPLANATORY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH.
- WHAT?
- OH, UH, NOTHING.
( clears throat )
OKAY, I'LL TRY TO EXPLAIN.
THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL IS
AN ANNUAL CELEBRATION.
THERE ARE FOOD STANDS
AND DIFFERENT EXHIBITS.
OTHER SCHOOLS DO IT TOO,
BUT OURS IS UNIQUE
BECAUSE WE HOLD
AN OPENING PARADE.
REPRESENTATIVES FROM EACH CLASS
DRESS UP IN COSTUME AND MARCH
FROM THE SHOPPING DISTRICT
TO THE TRAIN STATION AND BACK.
AND AFTER THE PARADE,
EVERYONE VOTES ON
THEIR FAVORITE COSTUMES.
- YEAH, THAT'S THE BEST PART
OF THE FESTIVAL.
ONE BOY AND ONE GIRL ARE CHOSEN
FOR THE GRAND PRIZE.
IT'S A PRESTIGIOUS AWARD
EVERYONE WANTS TO WIN.
- SURE, THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
- NOT REALLY YOUR THING, HUH?
- HUH?
- KONOE, YOU WERE ONE OF
THE PEOPLE CHOSEN TO REPRESENT
OUR CLASS IN THE PARADE.
- WHO ME?
- YEP.
YOU AND THE OTHERS LISTED
ON THE BOARD.
- UH...
- SORRY, I'M THE ONE
WHO NOMINATED YOU KONOE.
I FIGURED YOU'D BE PERFECT,
'CAUSE YOU'D LOOK GOOD
IN ANY COSTUME.
- WILL YOU BE WEARING
A COSTUME, TOO?
- GUESS SO.
SINCE EVERYBODY VOTED FOR ME.
- STUPID VOTE.
I DEMAND A RECOUNT.
- DON'T BE SUCH A SPOILSPORT.
IT'LL BE FUN.
- JUST SO YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO IT
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
- NO, I'LL DO IT.
- RIGHT ON.
THAT'S WHAT I WANNA HEAR.
- OKAY, NOW THAT
WE'VE CHOSEN OUR CAST.
WE JUST GOTTA DRAW
OUR ROLES, RIGHT?
YEAH.
SO THE THEMES CHOSEN FOR
OUR CLASS THIS YEAR ARE
"THE WIZARD OF OZ"
AND "ROMEO AND JULIET."
THE GUYS HAVE ALREADY
DRAWN THEIR ROLES.
TANAKA'S THE LION.
SATO'S THE TIN MAN.
I'M THE SCARECROW
AND SAKAI IS ROMEO.
- AND I JUST DREW TOTO SO IT
LOOKS LIKE I'LL BE JOINING
"THE WIZARD OF OZ" GROUP.
- THAT LEAVES THREE ROLES.
DOROTHY, THE WICKED WITCH
AND JULIET ARE STILL
UP FOR GRABS.
HERE, DRAW ONE.
- Ike: WONDERFUL.
WHY DOES YOSHIDA HAVE TO
BE ONE OF THE GIRLS UP
FOR THE PART OF SAKAI'S JULIET?
- I WONDER WHO'S GONNA BE
YOUR SWEETHEART.
- IT'S JUST FOR THE PARADE,
DUDE.
- IF I DRAW THE ROLE OF JULIET,
I'LL GET TO WALK IN THE PARADE
WITH SAKAI.
- ALL I WANT IS TO PLAY THE PART
OPPOSITE YUJI.
- ( gasping )
- GO AHEAD.
- HEY, CONGRATULATIONS.
- CONGRATULATIONS FOR WHAT?
- YOU GET TO PLAY SAKAI'S LOVE
INTEREST, YOU LUCKY DUCK.
YOU BEAT OUT BOTH
SHANA AND KONOE.
- IT'S NO SECRET, KAZUMI.
WE ALL KNOW YOU THREE ARE
VYING FOR HIS ATTENTION.
- YOU'RE BEING SILLY.
SERIOUSLY.  IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
- YOU'RE NOT HAPPY?
- IT'S JUST THAT, WELL,
I-- OF COURSE I'M HAPPY.
- ( laughing )
THERE WAS A TIME WHEN
I WOULD'VE BEEN THRILLED,
BUT THAT'S NOT TRUE ANYMORE.
NOW I KNOW THAT PLAYING
A ROLE ISN'T ENOUGH.
AND I'M SURE SHANA
FEELS THE SAME.
I KNOW YOU'RE PROBABLY
DISAPPOINTED,
BUT CHEER UP,
YOU'LL BE A PERFECT DOROTHY.
- YEAH, I'LL COME UP
WITH A GREAT COSTUME DESIGN.
- WEIRD.  KNOWING KAZUMI
WILL BE YUJI'S JULIET
DOESN'T BOTHER ME
LIKE I THOUGHT IT WOULD.
GUESS WE'VE FINALLY MOVED
BEYOND OUR PETTY JEALOUSY.
- I WANT SAKAI AND ME
TO BE SOMETHING MORE.
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE FUN
WITH THIS, RIGHT?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
DEEP DOWN I'M HAPPY, BUT--
- OH, HEY.
THINK KONOE'LL BE OKAY?
THE REST OF US GREW UP WATCHING
THE PARADE EVERY YEAR.
BUT SHE'S DRESSING UP
ON HER FIRST ONE.
MAYBE IF I SWITCHED OUT
OF MY ROLE AS ROMEO.
- YUJI, WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
THE PART OF ROMEO
IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
- OKAY.
- THERE'S NO REASON FOR YOU
TO SWITCH ROLES.
YOU'LL PLAY ROMEO
TO KAZUMI'S JULIET
AND THAT'S THAT, RIGHT?
- RIGHT, OF COURSE.  SORRY.
- THANKS, SHANA.
- ( telephone rings )
- ( grunting )
HOLD ON.  I'M COMING.
HELLO, SAKAI RESIDENCE.
YUJI, WHAT IS IT, DEAR?
- Ike: WE CAN ONLY WORK
AFTER SCHOOL UNTIL 6:00.
IF YOU NEED TO STAY LATER
THAN THAT FOR SOME REASON,
LET ME KNOW.
WE'LL BE ABLE TO STAY OVERNIGHT
ONCE WE GET CLOSER
- TO THE FESTIVAL.
- Class: OKAY!
- REALLY?  YOUR MOM'S
GONNA DONATE MATERIALS
FOR OUR PARADE COSTUMES?
HOW SWEET OF HER.
- SHE TOLD ME SHE PROBABLY
HAS MOST OF THE FABRIC
WE'RE GONNA NEED.
WE COULD PICK IT UP TODAY,
BUT I CAN'T DO IT.
I'M STUCK DOING STUFF UP HERE
ALL DAY.
- I'LL GO.
IT'D BE NICE TO GET OUT.
- YOU CAN'T CARRY IT ALL.
- MAYBE SHANA COULD COME
WITH ME?
- SURE.
- I KNOW.
I FEEL THE SAME.
- YOU'RE TRYING TO GET OUT
OF THE DOGHOUSE WITH SHANA.
- NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
MY MOM OFFERED 'CAUSE SHE
DOESN'T SEW AS MUCH
AS SHE USED TO.
WHAT?
- NOTHING, NOTHING AT ALL.
- Chigusa: GOODNESS.
YUJI'S PLAYING ROMEO?
NOT EXACTLY A PERFECT FIT.
- OH, I THINK HE'LL BE--
- I MEAN, WHY NOT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
ROMEO IS A PASSIONATE YOUNG MAN
SO IN LOVE WITH JULIET
THAT HE'S WILLING TO FOLLOW HER
ANYWHERE, EVEN INTO THE COLD,
DARK ARMS OF DEATH ITSELF.
THAT'S NOT MY YUJI.
- BUT ROMEO WAS SO DENSE
HE COULDN'T TELL JULIET
WAS REALLY DEAD.
YUJI'LL DO FINE.
- ( laughing )
- DON'T BE CYNICAL.
WHEN JULIET WAKES
TO FIND ROMEO DEAD,
SHE TAKES HER OWN LIFE.
THEIR LOVE WAS SO PURE.
THEY WANTED
TO BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
- OH.
- Chigusa: SHE'S RIGHT.
THAT'S A PART OF WHAT LOVE IS.
THE DESIRE TO BE CLOSE
TO A PERSON, NO MATTER WHAT.
ISN'T THAT HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT YUJI?
YOU JUST WANT
TO BE CLOSE TO HIM?
- I'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE
TO PUT IT INTO WORDS BEFORE,
BUT I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT IS HOW I FEEL.
- IT'S EMBARRASSING,
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT
I FEEL THAT WAY, TOO.
- IT'S HEARTBREAKING.
YOU CAN SEE THE PERSON YOU WANT
IN FRONT OF YOU,
BUT YOU CAN'T REACH HIM.
- IT'S LIKE
THERE'S AN INVISIBLE WALL.
ALL YOU WANNA DO
IS KNOCK IT DOWN,
BUT YOU CAN'T SEEM
TO MAKE IT BUDGE.
- YEAH, THAT'S IT.
- THAT WAS A GOOD ANALOGY,
SHANA.
JUST KNOW THAT IF YOU EVER
GET TIRED OF TRYING
TO BREAK THROUGH THAT WALL,
IT'S OKAY TO MOVE ON.
THAT JUST MEANS
IT WASN'T MEANT TO BE.
BUT IF YOU CHOOSE
TO KEEP FIGHTING
BECAUSE YOU TRULY WANT
TO BE CLOSE TO HIM.
IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL,
LISTEN TO YOUR HEART.
IT'LL TELL YOU WHAT TO DO.
YOU WANT TO STAY FOR DINNER?
YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME.
- Kazumi: WE SHOULD GO.
THANKS FOR THE INVITE, THOUGH.
- YES, THANK YOU.
- YOUR HEART WILL TELL
YOU WHAT TO DO.
WE'LL SEE.
- LISTEN, WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T LOOK BACK.
WE'RE BEING FOLLOWED.
IT'S NOT A DENIZEN.
BUT SOMEBODY'S BEEN TAILING US
EVER SINCE WE LEFT YUJI'S HOUSE.
I'M PRETTY SURE
WE CAN SHAKE HIM,
BUT YOU HAVE TO DO
EXACTLY AS I SAY.
- OKAY.
- HE ALMOST CAUGHT UP WITH US.
HE'S GOT SKILLS.
- WHO DO YOU THINK HE IS?
- WE'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
WE'RE GONNA TURN
THE TABLES ON HIM.
STRANGE.  HE SEEMS TO BE
HEADING BACK TOWARD YUJI'S.
IT MIGHT BE CHIGUSA HE'S AFTER.
LET'S TAKE A SHORTCUT.
- THAT DIDN'T TAKE AS LONG
AS I THOUGHT.
- ( gasps )
- ( shouts )
HE DODGED.
IDENTIFY YOURSELF.
- SHEESH.  YOU GOT ME GOOD.
WOW!  YOU SURE ARE STRONG,
LITTLE LADY.
- WHO THE--?
- WHAT THE HECK?
DAD, YOU'RE BACK?
- HE'S YOUR DAD?
- YEP, THAT'S ME.
KANTAROU SAKAI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- Chigusa:
WHEN WILL YOU LEARN?
YOUR LITTLE PRANKS JUST
AREN'T FUNNY, DEAR.
I WORRY THEY'LL END UP GETTING
YOU IN TROUBLE ONE DAY.
- FOR REAL, DAD.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU CAN'T JUST COME HOME
LIKE A NORMAL PERSON?
INSTEAD, YOU'RE FOLLOWING
MY FRIENDS
LIKE SOME
KIND OF CREEPY STALKER.
- YEAH, SORRY,
I'M AWAY SO MUCH.
CAN YOU BLAME ME
FOR BEING CURIOUS?
I JUST WANT TO SEE WHAT
MY ONLY SON'S BEEN UP TO
WHILE I'VE BEEN GONE
ON BUSINESS.
AND ANYHOW--
IT'S FUN.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
- PLEASE TRY
TO CONTROL YOURSELF, HON.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE FOLLOWING
PEOPLE.  YOU COULD SCARE THEM.
- I KNOW.  I KNOW.
BUT IT WAS STARTING
TO GET DARK OUT.
I WAS SIMPLY MAKING SURE THAT
THE GIRLS WHO ARE NICE ENOUGH
TO LOOK AFTER MY BOY
MADE IT HOME SAFELY.
THOUGH, I CAN SEE NOW, THEY
DIDN'T REALLY NEED MY HELP.
( laughs )
- YOU ASKED FOR IT.
LET ME MAKE IT UP
TO YOU LADIES
WITH A NICE HOME-COOKED MEAL.
- OKAY.
- THANKS FOR THE FOOD.
- IT MAY SEEM STRANGE,
BUT IT'S TRADITION FOR US
TO SERVE OUR MEALS FAMILY-STYLE.
WELL, KANTAROU'S TRADITION.
- THIS WAY EVERYBODY
GETS A TASTE
OF EACH OF THE DIFFERENT DISHES.
IT JUST MAKES MORE SENSE TO ME.
- YOU GUYS BETTER HURRY.  FOOD
DISAPPEARS QUICKLY AROUND HERE.
- YES, PLEASE HELP YOURSELVES.
- IT'S DELICIOUS.
CAN'T TELL YOU HOW MUCH
I'VE MISSED YOUR COOKING.
- OH, IT'S JUST LEFTOVERS.
- OH, YEAH?
WELL, IT'S SO GOOD
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW IT.
- EXCUSE ME.
I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE.
YOU TWO LOOK TOO YOUNG
TO HAVE A TEENAGER.
- YOU THINK SO?
- THANK YOU.
- MY DAD KNOCKED MY MOM UP
WHEN THEY WERE STILL STUDENTS.
- WOW, THEY WERE THAT YOUNG?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY WERE JUST KIDS WHEN
THEY DECIDED TO GET HITCHED.
- MARRIED AS STUDENTS.
ISN'T THAT ROMANTIC?
- IT MAY SOUND ROMANTIC,
BUT MARRIAGE IS A BIG STEP
TO TAKE WHEN NEITHER OF YOU
HAS FINISHED GROWING UP.
I KNOW YOU'RE CURIOUS,
BUT PLEASE DON'T ASK US
HOW OLD WE ARE.  CHIGUSA WOULD
THROW AN ABSOLUTE FIT.
- HUSH.  YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT TROUBLE TONIGHT.
- ( laughing )
- YUJI, WOULD YOU MIND CLEARING
THE TABLE FOR ME?
I'M GONNA MAKE SOME COFFEE.
- SURE.
SHANA AND YOSHIDA WENT OUTSIDE
WITH DAD.
I WONDER WHAT
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- DON'T WORRY.
- I HOPE HE DOESN'T
EMBARRASS ME.
- GOTTA SAY,
THAT'S TRULY A GEM
OF WISDOM SHE GAVE YOU.
"LISTEN TO YOUR HEART AND IT
WILL TELL YOU WHAT TO DO."
THAT'S MY CHIGUSA FOR YOU.
- I'M SORRY.
I HATE TO PRY.
BUT WATCHING THE TWO
OF YOU INTERACT,
IT'S OBVIOUS YOU HAVE
A GREAT RELATIONSHIP.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU MIGHT
HAVE ADVICE FOR US.
- I DON'T KNOW, GIRLS.
I'M NOT WISE ENOUGH
TO BE HANDING OUT ADVICE
TO OTHERS.
BUT I'M FLATTERED
YOU ASKED ME.  THANKS.
- THAT DOESN'T HELP US.
- HMM?
- YOSHIDA WASN'T TRYING
TO FLATTER YOU.
WE NEED TO KNOW.
- IS THAT SO?
WELL, THEN LET ME THINK.
CHIGUSA AND I WERE
SO YOUNG WHEN WE MET.
WE LOST OUR WAY A FEW TIMES,
BUT WE NEVER GAVE UP.
SOMEHOW, WE ALWAYS MANAGED TO
FIND OUR WAY BACK TO EACH OTHER.
'CAUSE LIKE SHE TOLD
YOU EARLIER, WE LISTENED
TO OUR HEARTS
AND THEY TOLD US WHAT TO DO.
YOU WANNA KNOW WHY OUR MARRIAGE
HAS BEEN SUCCESSFUL?
JUST BETWEEN US?
- MM-HMM.
- IT'S BECAUSE SHE HELD ON.
LIKE THIS!
- ( gasping )
- ( laughs )
LIKE MOST MEN IN MY FAMILY,
I WANTED TO FLY FREE AS A KITE
AND NEVER BE TIED DOWN,
BUT SHE GRABBED MY KITE STRING
AND HELD ON FOR DEAR LIFE.
AND AS LONG AS SHE KEEPS
HOLDING,
I'LL NEVER BE LOST.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
UP TO OUT THERE?
YOU'RE NOT FILLING
THEIR HEADS WITH MORE
OF YOUR SILLY STORIES,
NOW ARE YOU?
- OF COURSE NOT.
THIS IS A VERY IMPORTANT STORY.
- IF YOU SAY SO.
WELL, COFFEE'S READY
WHENEVER YOU WANT IT.
- WELL, SHALL WE?
IF YOU FIND
YOU'RE FEELING LOST,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
REACH OUT.  YOU NEVER KNOW.
THERE MIGHT BE SOMEONE
REACHING OUT TO YOU AS WELL.
COME ON, GIRLS.
IT'S COFFEE TIME.
CHIGUSA'S IS THE BEST
YOU'LL EVER TASTE.
- IF YOU FIND YOU'RE
FEELING LOST...
- YOU HAVE TO REACH OUT.
- I KNEW IT.  I HAD A FEELING
PHELES WAS STILL ALIVE.
- YES, SHE'S STILL ALIVE.
BUT SHE'S NOT HERE.
SHE'S OUT SEARCHING.
- FOR WHAT?
- THE TREASURE TOOL.
COME NOW.
WHAT WOULD YOU EXPECT OF PHELES?
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD IS
A MEMENTO OF HER LOST LOVER.
SHE'S GOING TO FIND
THAT MYSTES.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
- BUT IF THAT
SHOULD COME TO PASS...
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL
IS QUICKLY APPROACHING.
TO FINISH PREPARATIONS,
OUR CLASS IS ALLOWED
TO SPEND THE NIGHT AT SCHOOL.
SHANA JOINS IN ON THE FUN
LIKE ANY OTHER STUDENT.
THAT IS, UNTIL WILHELMINA
RETURNS WITH NEWS.
SHE TELLS US THE TALE OF PHELES
AND HER "ETERNAL LOVER" JOHAN,
THE CREATORS OF
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
DANGER LOOMS ON THE HORIZON.
NEXT TIME ON
"SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II"...
"THE PROMISED PAIR."