- Alastor:
SHANA'S UNUSUAL BEHAVIOR
CAUSED WILHELMINA TO BECOME
CONCERNED ABOUT HER WELL-BEING.
THANKS TO A COOKING LESSON FROM
CHIGUSA, WILHELMINA WAS ABLE
TO CREATE A HOME-COOKED MEAL
THAT HELPED CHEER SHANA UP.
HOWEVER, THINGS ARE NOT
COMPLETELY BACK TO NORMAL.
SHANA AND KAZUMI ARE STILL
FUMING WITH JEALOUSY
BECAUSE OF YUJI'S TIME
SPENT ALONE WITH KONOE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- YOU'VE BEEN LATE
EVERY MORNING THIS WEEK.
- YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- Yuji: YOU THINK
I'M SPENDING TOO MUCH TIME
WITH KONOE?  YOU'VE SEEN
HOW HELPLESS SHE IS.
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN LEAVE HER
TO HER OWN DEVICES, YOU KNOW.
- I THINK YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT HERE, BUDDY.
YOU DON'T SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON AROUND YOU.
JUST TRY NOT TO SPEND
SO MUCH TIME WITH HER.
- THAT'S WEIRD.
- HEY, KONOE.
- HUH?
- NOW THAT OGATA'S HERE
TO WALK YOU TO AND FROM SCHOOL,
MAYBE YOU DON'T NEED
MY HELP ANYMORE.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING, SAKAI?
ARE YOU TRYING TO DITCH HER
AND LEAVE HER TO ME?
- NO, THAT'S NOT IT
AT ALL.
I'LL STILL HELP YOU OUT WITH HER
AT SCHOOL AND STUFF.  IT'S JUST
I FEEL BAD ABOUT MAKING YOU GUYS
WAIT FOR ME EVERY MORNING.
- ( students chattering )
- GOOD MORNING.
- MAYBE YOSHIDA
IS UPSET WITH ME
BECAUSE SHE WANTED
TO KEEP LOOKING AFTER KONOE.
BUT...
- ( Shana sighs )
- THAT DOESN'T EXPLAIN
WHY SHANA'S MAD AT ME.
IT SEEMS LIKE SHE'S LEFT
MY TRAINING UP TO WILHELMINA.
- ( clock chiming )
- EVERYBODY TAKE
YOUR SEATS.
- UH, I HATE TO TELL YOU,
BUT I JUST FOUND OUT YOU'RE ALL
GOING TO HAVE A ROUND OF TESTS
IN EACH OF YOUR CLASSES
TOMORROW.
- BUT YOU CAN'T JUST SPRING THAT
ON US WITHOUT ANY WARNING.
- YEAH, WE NEED TIME
TO STUDY AND PREPARE.
- THE ONLY WAY WE CAN TELL
WHO ACTUALLY STUDIED
OVER SUMMER BREAK IS TO TEST YOU
ON THAT INFORMATION.
THESE TESTS WILL TOUCH
ON EVERYTHING YOU WERE TAUGHT
THE FIRST SEMESTER.  NOW LET'S
TAKE A LOOK AT THAT SCHEDULE.
- Tanaka: I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE PULLING THIS CRAP ON US.
POP QUIZZES ARE JUST EVIL,
YOU KNOW?
- IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S
ANYTHING WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO TRY
AND FAKE IT THE BEST WE CAN.
- GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT.
SWEATING IT
WON'T DO ME ANY GOOD.
- EXCUSE ME, IKE,
I HAVE A SMALL FAVOR
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU.
WOULD YOU BE AT ALL
WILLING TO TUTOR ME?
AN OVERNIGHT CRAM SESSION
WITH YOU WOULD GIVE ME
A BETTER CHANCE OF PASSING
THAN IF I STUDY ALONE.
PLEASE HELP.
- WELL, I GUESS THAT WOULDN'T BE
A PROBLEM, BUT--
WAIT, DID YOU SAY OVERNIGHT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YEAH, WE CAN MAKE IT
A SLEEPOVER.
NOW WHERE CAN WE GO?
WHAT ABOUT SATO'S?
- HUH?
- SO, TANAKA,
WANT TO JOIN US?
- MM-HMM.
YOU SHOULD DO IT, BIG GUY.
YOU NEED TO STUDY.
- SHUT UP, JERK FACE.
- AN OVERNIGHT STUDY SESSION?
WELL, OKAY.
YOU CAN COUNT ME IN,
BUT ONLY IF THE REST
OF THE GANG CAN COME OVER
TO STUDY TOO.
- OKAY, GUESS I'LL GO UP
AND ASK 'EM.
SO ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA JOIN US?
- I DON'T GET WHY WE ALL
HAVE TO STUDY TOGETHER.
I THINK I'D PREFER TO STUDY
FOR THE TESTS ON MY OWN.
- BUT IF WE ALL
STUDY TOGETHER,
WE CAN HELP EACH OTHER
WITH THE DIFFICULT STUFF.
SO ARE YOU GONNA GO,
YOSHIDA?
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- WHO ELSE
WILL BE THERE?
- WELL, IT'LL BE
THE USUAL SUSPECTS, YOU KNOW--
IKE, SATO,
TANAKA AND OGATA.
HOPEFULLY THE TWO OF YOU
LADIES.
AND I'LL BE THERE,
OF COURSE.
- AND?
AND KONOE.
- WHY ARE YOU SO ANGRY,
MILADY?
WAS IT MY COOKING?
DID YOU NOT LIKE
THE BACON AND EGGS I MADE?
- IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT.
- THEN WHAT--?
- IT'S NOTHING, OKAY?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
AND DON'T BE LATE
FOR YUJI'S TRAINING.
- ( door closes )
- WHATEVER IT IS, IT MUST HAVE
SOMETHING TO DO WITH THE MYSTES.
HE STOPPED BY TO SPEAK WITH ME
A FEW MINUTES AGO.
- WHAT DID HE SAY?
- HE SAID HE WANTS TO SKIP
TONIGHT'S TRAINING
TO ATTEND A STUDY SESSION
WITH YOU.
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S
SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
I WORRY THE MYSTES IS NOT
TAKING HIS SITUATION SERIOUSLY.
HIS TRAINING
IS MUCH MORE VITAL.
- Tiamat: UTTER NONSENSE.
- Alastor: YOU CANNOT
LEAVE YUJI SAKAI'S TRAINING
TO THE SPECIALIST
OF EVERYTHING
AND THE TIARA OF DREAMS
AND ILLUSIONS FOREVER.
I THINK IT'S TIME
YOU TOOK THE REINS AGAIN.
HOW LONG DO YOU INTEND
TO KEEP UP THIS STUBBORN ACT?
- I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
- Eita: PLEASE,
WE'RE BEGGING YOU, MARGERY.
IT'S JUST FOR ONE NIGHT.
COME ON, GET UP, WOULD YOU?
- STOP YELLING AT ME.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
I HAVE TO LEAVE THE HOUSE.
- WE ALREADY TOLD YOU, WE'VE GOT
FRIENDS COMING OVER TO STUDY.
YOU TRY IT, SAKAI.
SHE'S NOT GONNA LISTEN TO US.
- IF SHE WANTS TO SLEEP,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST TRY
MOVING HER
TO ANOTHER ROOM?
- DO YOU WANT HER STUMBLING
IN HERE ALL DRUNK LATER?
- BESIDES, IF SHE
RUNS INTO OGATA,
IT COULD CAUSE
SOME MAJOR PROBLEMS.
UH, LONG STORY.
- ( Margery moans )
- ( Marcosias laughing )
THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY, BOYS.
WHEN THE BOTTOMLESS KEG,
A.K.A. MARGERY DAW,
IS THIS DRUNK,
SHE WON'T GET UP FOR ANYTHING.
A DENIZEN COULD APPEAR
AND SHE'D--
OW!
- OKAY, THAT'S SCARY.
SHE RESPONDS TO MARCO
EVEN WHEN SHE'S DEAD ASLEEP.
- ( doorbell rings )
- DAMN IT.  OUT OF TIME, GUYS.
- I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO HIDE HER
AND HOPE
SHE DOESN'T WAKE UP
ANYTIME SOON.
WELCOME TO MY
HUMBLE ABODE.
- WHAT'S WITH
ALL THE GROCERIES?
- WELL, I FIGURED I WOULD BE
IN CHARGE OF COOKING.
IF WE'RE GOING TO BE STUDYING
LATE INTO THE NIGHT,
WE'RE BOUND TO GET HUNGRY
AT SOME POINT.
- I OFFERED TO LEND HER
A HELPING HAND IN THE KITCHEN,
BUT IKE WON'T LET ME.
- YOU HAVE TO STUDY.
YOU'RE THE WHOLE REASON WE'RE
EVEN HAVING THIS CRAM SESSION.
- HE'S RIGHT.
THIS WAS YOUR IDEA.
- LET YOSHIDA HANDLE IT.
SHE HAS GOOD GRADES
AND SHE'S AN AWESOME COOK.
CAN'T SAY THE SAME FOR YOU.
- TANAKA!
- SATO, WOULD YOU MIND
SHOWING ME TO THE KITCHEN?
- I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
- Hayato: WOW, I HEARD
THAT YOU HAD A HUGE PLACE,
BUT I WASN'T EXPECTING
THIS AT ALL.
- WELL, I TRY NOT TO MAKE
A BIG DEAL ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW?
HOW'S THE A.C.?
IS THE TEMPERATURE OKAY?
OH, AND IF YOU WANT SOMETHING
TO DRINK, PLEASE HELP YOURSELF.
- ALL RIGHT, I GUESS
WE'D BETTER GET STARTED.  I KNOW
WE'VE GOT ALL NIGHT, BUT WE'VE
GOT A LOT OF GROUND TO COVER.
- LET'S DO IT.  I'M READY
WHENEVER YOU GUYS ARE.
- I GOT THIS.
- THERE'S AN EASIER WAY
TO SOLVE IT.  TRY USING
THIS EQUATION INSTEAD.
ONCE YOU SUBSTITUTE THIS ONE,
YOU CAN SEE HOW EASY
IT COMES TOGETHER.
- THIS WORD PROBLEM SHOULD BE
FAIRLY EASY.  WANT TO TRY?
- IT MAKES
MY BRAIN HURT.
- SEE?
PRETTY EASY, RIGHT?
- ( giggles )
- PERFECT.
HOPE THEY'RE HUNGRY.
- Ogata: WHOA!
DID YOU SERIOUSLY MAKE
ALL OF THIS BY YOURSELF?
- YEP, AND THERE'S SECONDS ON
THE RICE AND THE MISO SOUP.
- All: THANKS FOR DINNER,
YOSHIDA.
- OH, WOW, THIS MAY BE THE BEST
STIR-FRY I'VE EVER TASTED.
OMELET'S AWESOME TOO.
IT'S ALL SO GOOD, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO EAT NEXT.
- I HAD NO IDEA YOU ATE LIKE A
FREAKING KING EVERY DAY, SAKAI.
MAN, YOU ARE
ONE LUCKY BASTARD.
- SO HOW DOES IT TASTE,
SHANA?
- FINE.  IT'LL DO.
- HEY, KONOE, YOU WANT
TO SPLIT THIS WITH ME?
- OH, YES,
THANK YOU.
- ( all giggling )
- Ogata: IT REALLY WAS
DELICIOUS.
YOU'LL HAVE TO TEACH ME
A FEW TRICKS.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO HELP.
I CAN HANDLE THE DISHES.
- OH, COME ON.
IT'S THE LEAST I CAN DO
AFTER YOU COOKED US
SUCH AN AMAZING MEAL.
IT WOULDN'T BE FAIR TO LEAVE
ALL THE CLEAN-UP TO YOU.
- NO BIG DEAL.
SATO HAS A DISHWASHER.
- YEAH, BUT THAT THING IS
A LITTLE TEMPERAMENTAL.
IF YOU DON'T LOAD IT
PERFECTLY,
THEN WATER STARTS
LEAKING OUT OF IT.
- IF YOU PUSH THAT BUTTON OVER
THERE, IT'LL TURN ON THE POWER.
I KNOW MY WAY
AROUND THIS PLACE.
SATO AND I
HAVE BEEN FRIENDS
SINCE WE WERE WAY BACK
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL.
TANAKA HUNG OUT
A LOT TOO.
OH, WOW,
I MISS THOSE DAYS.
WE DIDN'T HAVE A CARE
IN THE WORLD BACK THEN.
- ( moans )
HELP ME.
WATER.
- MARGERY?  OH, HEY.
- KAZUMI.
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
AND WHO IN THE HELL
ARE YOU?
- ( screaming )
- WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN "IT'S"
AND "ITS" WITHOUT
THE APOSTROPHE?
- WITH AN APOSTROPHE
IS A CONTRACTION.
WITHOUT AN APOSTROPHE,
"ITS" IS POSSESSIVE.
- BUT HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN
TO USE ONE OR THE OTHER?
- WELL, THAT IS DEPENDENT UPON
THE STRUCTURE OF YOUR SENTENCE.
- WELL, CAN'T YOU GIVE ME SOME
KIND OF EXAMPLE OR SOMETHING?
( screams )
DAMN IT, SATO, STOP BEING LAZY
AND STUDY WITH US!
- THE DINNER
MADE ME SO TIRED.
- I SWEAR YOU ARE
TOTALLY HOPELESS, MAN.
WHAT'S TAKING OGATA
AND YOSHIDA SO LONG?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THEM.
OGATA'S BEEN HERE
MILLIONS OF TIMES, SO IT'S NOT
LIKE THEY'RE GONNA GET LOST.
- BUT IT'S BEEN 30 MINUTES.
DISHES SHOULDN'T TAKE THAT LONG.
- UH, HOLD UP A SEC, KONOE.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'M GOING
TO CHECK ON THEM.
- WHY DON'T YOU
LET ME DO THAT?
- BUT IF THEY'RE STILL CLEANING,
I SHOULD HELP THEM,
ESPECIALLY AFTER YOSHIDA COOKED
SUCH A DELICIOUS MEAL.
- I'LL GO TOO.  BET THEY COULD
USE AN EXTRA SET OF HANDS.
- Shana: I'LL GO WITH HER.
YUJI, YOU STAY HERE
AND STUDY.
- UH, EXCUSE ME.
- I AM NOT GONNA LET HER
BE ALONE WITH YUJI.
Shana:
THIS IS BIZARRE.
YOSHIDA WOULD NEVER ABANDON
THE DISHES HALFWAY THROUGH.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I THOUGHT I'D GO AHEAD
AND CLEAN UP THE REST.
- YOU DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
( sighs ) YOU'VE NEVER ACTUALLY
WASHED DISHES BEFORE, HAVE YOU?
FIRST, YOU HAVE TO
TURN ON THE WATER.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
JUST WATCH ME.
NEXT, YOU GOTTA PUT SOAP
ON THE SPONGE.
IF YOUR HANDS GET MESSY,
JUST GRAB A PAPER TOWEL.
- ( ice clinks )
- SO WHAT BRINGS YOU
TO THIS NECK OF THE WOODS,
MISS OMEGA?
- MY NAME IS OGATA--
MATAKE OGATA.
- THESE JAPANESE NAMES
ARE HARD TO REMEMBER.
THEY ALL
SOUND THE SAME.
- KAZUMI, YOU AREN'T FRIENDS
WITH THIS CRAZY LADY, ARE YOU?
- WELL, KINDA.
- ( groans )
WHAT IS HER DEAL?
SHE'S ACTING LIKE
SHE OWNS THE PLACE,
AND SHE DOESN'T EVEN
LIVE HERE.
- UM, I DON'T KNOW.
- THE NAME'S MARGERY DAW.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
HERE'S A THOUGHT: YOU GOT
A QUESTION-- JUST ASK IT.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
ARE YOU INTERESTED IN TANAKA?
- OGATA.
- THAT WAS RUDE.
I'M SORRY.
- ( chuckles ) I THINK I KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
- JUST ANSWER
THE QUESTION.
I SAW YOU TOGETHER.
YOU AND TANAKA
WERE WALKING SIDE BY SIDE
AT THE MISAGO FESTIVAL.
- YOU SAW KEISAKU
WITH US TOO, RIGHT?
NO NEED TO WORRY.
I LIKE THE TWO OF THEM,
BUT NOT ROMANTICALLY.
I CAME TO THIS CITY ON BUSINESS
RATHER UNEXPECTEDLY.
KEISAKU WAS NICE ENOUGH
TO OFFER ME A PLACE TO STAY
UNTIL I CAN ARRANGE A SUITABLE
RESIDENCE OF MY OWN.
IN THE MEANTIME, I HAVE THOSE
TWO HELPING ME WITH ODD JOBS
EVERY NOW AND THEN,
BUT THAT'S AS FAR AS IT GOES.
- IS IT NOW?
- YEP.
THEY MAY FEEL MORE FOR ME
THAN I DO THEM,
BUT IT'S CERTAINLY NOT
THAT KIND OF LOVE.
THEY THINK OF ME
MORE LIKE A SISTER.
YOU CAN SEE IT IN THEIR EYES.
IT'S PURELY INNOCENT.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
ROMANTIC LOVE OR AFFECTION.
THEY SIMPLY ADMIRE ME
AS YOUNG PEOPLE
OFTEN ADMIRE THEIR ELDERS.
YOU GET IT NOW?
SO TELL ME, WHAT'S A CUTE GIRL
LIKE YOURSELF SEE IN THAT
BIG OAF ANYWAY?  EITA'S NOT
EXACTLY THE SMARTEST KID AROUND.
- I DON'T KNOW.  WE'RE FRIENDS.
I'M SO SORRY I WAS RUDE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I UNDERSTAND.
JEALOUSY IS JUST ANOTHER PART
OF BEING IN LOVE.
LOVE IS LIKE A MIRROR
THAT REFLECTS
BOTH YOUR GOOD
AND BAD SIDES,
ESPECIALLY IF YOUR LOVE
IS UNREQUITED.
THEN YOU CAN BECOME ENVIOUS,
JEALOUS, EVEN RESENTFUL.
IT CAN BE TOUGH.  YOU HAVE TO
FACE ALL KINDS OF EMOTIONS.
- HAVE YOU FELT
THAT WAY?
- WE ALL HAVE.  THERE'S NO
REASON TO FEEL ASHAMED.
IT JUST SHOWS HOW SERIOUS
YOU ARE ABOUT THE ONE YOU LOVE.
TELL YOU WHAT:
I'LL SHARE THE SECRET OF HOW
TO GET THROUGH THIS JEALOUSY
CRAP WITHOUT LOSING YOUR MIND.
TO BE HONEST, IT'S NOT
ALL THAT DIFFICULT.
YOU NEED TO UNDERSTAND THE OTHER
PERSON.  IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
AND DON'T MAKE
ANY HARSH JUDGMENTS,
'CAUSE THINGS AREN'T ALWAYS
WHAT THEY SEEM.
WELL, BEST OF LUCK,
YOUNG MAIDENS.
I HOPE IT WORKS OUT.
- JEEZ, WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON AROUND HERE?
WHERE DID ALL THE GIRLS
RUN OFF TO?
THIS TURNED INTO
A TOTAL SAUSAGE FEST.
- IT IS TAKING THEM
A LONG TIME TO CLEAN UP.
SHOULD WE CHECK ON 'EM?
- NAH, I'D LEAVE THEM BE.
THEY'RE PROBABLY JUST
SHARING SOME GIRL TALK.
- I'M NOT SAYING
I'M GOING IN THERE.
- IT'S NICE AND QUIET.
I LIKE HANGING OUT WITH JUST
THE BOYS SOMETIMES.
WE SHOULDN'T TAKE
THESE TIMES FOR GRANTED.
WE'LL ALL GO
OUR OWN WAYS SOON.
WE MAY NEVER GET TO SIT
TOGETHER LIKE THIS AGAIN.
- Yuji: SATO'S WORDS
REALLY STRUCK ME.
HE WAS RIGHT.
I DIDN'T PLAN ON STAYING
IN MISAKI CITY FOREVER.
THIS MOMENT
MAY NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
- WHAT'S WITH YOU, GUYS?
YOU'RE ALL QUIET AND DEPRESSED
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
- ( bang )
- ( girls scream )
- SHANA!
- KONOE!
- THAT DISHWASHER.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU FORGET TO TELL THEM
HOW TO LOAD IT?
AND WHY ARE THEY DOING DISHES?
I THOUGHT YOU HAD IT COVERED.
- WELL, WE STARTED,
BUT WE GOT DISTRACTED.
- HELP ME OUT, YUJI.
PLEASE JUST MAKE IT STOP.
- LET ME TRY
THE VALVE.
- ( sighs ) THAT SHOULD DO IT.
YOU OKAY?
- YEAH.
- HOW DID THIS HAPPEN EXACTLY?
- KONOE'S THE ONE
WHO TOLD ME TO.
- I DON'T MEAN TO LAUGH.
I'M SORRY,
BUT IT'S REALLY FUNNY.
- I'M GLAD EVERYONE'S OKAY.
I WAS KIND OF WORRIED
AFTER HEARING THOSE
BLOOD-CURDLING SCREAMS.
- KONOE'S LAUGHING,
SO I GUESS IT'S ALL GOOD.
- YEAH, BUT SHANA DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE SHE'S TOO HAPPY ABOUT IT.
- Marcosias: LOOKS LIKE
EVERYTHING IS BACK TO NORMAL.
GOOD JOB, MARGERY.
- I DIDN'T DO MUCH.
I JUST GAVE THEM SOME ADVICE
THAT HELPED ME
WHEN I WAS THEIR AGE.
- SERIOUSLY?
ADVICE YOU GOT AS A TEEN
IS STILL RELEVANT
AFTER HUNDREDS OF YEARS?
OW!
- STUPID MARCO, SHUT YOUR TRAP.
- ( clock chiming )
- TOTALLY BOMBED IT.
- YEAH, WE SHOULD'VE
GONE BACK TO STUDYING
AFTER THE WHOLE WATER INCIDENT.
- WIPE OFF THE FROWNY FACE.
OUR TEST SCORES AREN'T
THE ONLY THING THAT CAME OUT OF
OUR STUDY SESSION, TANAKA.
- THERE'S BEEN
A MAJOR CHANGE WITH KONOE.
SEEMS YOSHIDA AND SHANA
ARE BOTH MAKING ATTEMPTS
TO GET ALONG WITH HER.
WHERE DID THEY--?
- THEY WENT UP ON THE ROOF
AGAIN FOR A MINUTE.
- SOMETHING THEY NEEDED
TO TAKE CARE OF.
- THEY SAID
THEY'D BE RIGHT BACK,
SO THERE'S NO NEED TO WAIT FOR
THEM TO START EATING.
- THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
SAID THAT?
- SHE SAID
IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT WE ALL TRY AND
UNDERSTAND ONE ANOTHER.
SHE SAID THAT IF YOUR LOVE
IS UNREQUITED,
THEN SOMETIMES YOU START
TO FEEL JEALOUS OF OTHERS.
BUT THERE'S NO NEED
TO BE ASHAMED,
BECAUSE THAT JUST PROVES
HOW MUCH YOU REALLY CARE.
MARGERY SAID A LOT.
IT WAS ALL VERY HELPFUL.
- SO WHAT'S YOUR POINT
IN TELLING ME ALL THIS?
- IT'S INFO I THOUGHT
I SHOULD PASS ALONG,
'CAUSE I FELT THAT WAY
TOWARDS YOU
AND I DON'T WANT OUR
FRIENDSHIP TO BE RUINED
BECAUSE I COULDN'T
GET OVER IT.
- Shana: SO WE NEED TO TRY
TO UNDERSTAND ONE ANOTHER.
I NEED TO UNDERSTAND
YUJI'S DESIRE TO HELP KONOE
INSTEAD OF
GETTING JEALOUS OF THEM.
- ( running footsteps )
- COME ON, SHANA.
LET'S JOIN THE OTHERS
FOR LUNCH.
- I'LL HAVE TO BE
HARDER ON YOU
TO MAKE UP FOR YESTERDAY'S
MISSED TRAINING SESSION.
- IS THAT REALLY NECESSARY?
I TOLD YOU, WE WERE STUDYING.
- I HOPE YOU'RE READY FOR THIS.
- Tiamat: EN GARDE.
- Shana: WILHELMINA.
- WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- WE ARE IN THE MIDDLE OF
TRAINING, MILADY.
- I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
I'M INTERESTED TO SEE JUST HOW
MUCH YOU'VE LEARNED FROM HER.
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
GLAD YOU'RE BACK.
- Shana:
I WANT TO UNDERSTAND YUJI
BECAUSE OF THE WAY
I FEEL.
BUT EVEN MORE THAN THAT,
I WANT TO KNOW
HOW HE REALLY FEELS
ABOUT ME.
SO I'M GONNA STICK CLOSE TO HIM
UNTIL I FINALLY FIND OUT.
- ARE YOU READY?
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: MY BUDDY IKE
HAS ALREADY TOLD ME
HE'S GOT FEELINGS
FOR YOSHIDA,
BUT MAKING A CONFESSION OF LOVE
ISN'T EASY FOR ANYBODY,
NOT EVEN THE SMARTEST GUY
IN CLASS.
IN AN ATTEMPT TO TRY AND MAKE IT
A LITTLE EASIER ON HIMSELF,
IKE COMES UP WITH A NEW PROJECT
AND PLANS IT OUT TO A TEE.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"IKE HAYATO,
HIS DAY OF GLORY".