- Alastor: FUMINA KONOE WAS
RAISED LIKE A SPOILED PRINCESS,
BUT SINCE MOVING TO MISAKI, SHE
HAS BECOME DEPENDENT ON YUJI.
SHE WILL NOT LEAVE
HIS SIDE,
UNABLE TO PERFORM EVEN THE
SIMPLEST TASK WITHOUT HIS HELP.
KAZUMI AND SHANA
FEEL SLIGHTED
THAT YUJI SPENDS ALL OF HIS
FREE TIME WITH FUMINA.
THE GIRLS TRY TO FIGHT BACK
THEIR JEALOUSY,
BUT IT IS
A CONSTANT STRUGGLE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( exclaiming )
OW, OW, OW, OW.
WHAT THE--?
IT DOESN'T ACTUALLY HURT.
DOESN'T EVEN LOOK
LIKE I'M INJURED.
- INDEED, YOU ARE BECOMING
STRONGER AND LEARNING
TO CONTROL THE FLOW OF YOUR
POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- Tiamat: TO MANIPULATE IT.
- AND THAT KEEPS ME
FROM GETTING HURT?
- THANKS FOR ALL YOUR HELP
WITH MY TRAINING.
SO HOW'S SHANA DOING?
- WHY DO YOU ASK ME,
WHEN YOU SEE HER AT SCHOOL?
- Tiamat: ALMOST EVERY DAY.
- I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'VE GOT SOME IDEA
WHY SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO TRAIN ME ANYMORE, DO YOU?
I'VE TRIED TO ASK HER,
BUT SHE REFUSES TO TELL ME.
- THE MISTRESS STATED
SHE IS SIMPLY OCCUPIED
WITH OTHER THINGS AT THE MOMENT.
- NO PRYING, YOUNG MAN.
- YEAH, I GET IT.
SORRY.
- MORE TRAINING TOMORROW.
HE WAS ABLE TO DODGE
A DIRECT HIT FROM ME--
IMPRESSIVE INDEED.
- Tiamat: AND THEN HE FELL DOWN.
QUITE A BLUNDER
ON HIS PART, YES.
MY POINT IS,
HE'S COME A LONG WAY
IN HIS TRAINING.
HE IS NOW ABLE TO REGENERATE
HIS POWER IN BATTLE.
- ( clock ticking )
- YOUR RAMEN IS READY.
- Tiamat: TIME'S UP.
- HMM.
- A CUP OF NOODLES AGAIN?
- AFTER TRYING VARIOUS COOKING
STYLES FOR A HOME-COOKED MEAL,
MY CONCLUSION IS THAT
THIS IS MOST EFFICIENT.
- Tiamat: NO COOKING REQUIRED.
- Alastor: THAT MAY BE TRUE,
HOWEVER, I BELIEVE HAVING
THE SAME MEAL NIGHT AFTER NIGHT
LACKS WHAT THE HUMANS CALL
"VARIETY."
- ALASTOR, THIS VARIETY
YOU SPEAK OF
IS UNNECESSARY
FOR FLAME HAZE.
WON'T YOU FINISH
YOUR RAMEN, MILADY?
- BATH TIME.
- ( Yuji's voice )
SHANA, WAIT UP!
WHAT ARE YOU
SO ANGRY ABOUT?
- ( Shana's voice )
I'M NOT ANGRY ABOUT ANYTHING.
- DON'T LIE TO ME.
- I'M NOT LYING.
IT'S JUST THAT I--
- I WISH I COULD TELL HIM.
- THE MISTRESS HAS LEFT HER
CLOTHES ON THE FLOOR YET AGAIN.
MOST UNCOUTH INDEED, TO LEAVE
SUCH SIMPLE TASKS TO OTHERS.
- Tiamat: THE MISTRESS
IS LAZY.
- Shana: I PICK UP AFTER MYSELF.
- INDEED, MILADY, YOU DO NOT.
- SHUT UP.
YES, I DO.
- FORGIVE MY ASKING, MILADY,
BUT HOW MUCH LONGER
DO YOU PLAN TO LEAVE
THE MYSTES'S TRAINING TO ME?
I'VE CONTINUED THIS LONG WITHOUT
ANY EXPLANATION FROM YOU.
- WOULD YOU PLEASE
JUST KEEP DOING IT?
'CAUSE I DON'T WANNA!
- YELLING WILL NOT CHANGE
THE SITUATION IN ANY WAY.
- Tiamat: IT'S ACTUALLY
QUITE RUDE.
- INDEED, YOU HAVE DONE
NOTHING BUT YELL
FOR THE PAST THREE DAYS.
IT LEADS ME TO BELIEVE
YOU ARE DISTRESSED--
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU I'M FINE!
JEEZ, JUST LEAVE ME ALONE,
WOULD YOU?
YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M FEELING RIGHT NOW
EVEN IF I TOLD YOU.  ALL YOUR
NAGGING ABOUT CHORES AND YUJI--
IT'S JUST FRUSTRATING ME
EVEN MORE.
SO THE BEST THING
YOU COULD DO RIGHT NOW
IS JUST
LEAVE ME ALONE!
- ( door opens and closes )
- I ALWAYS SEE YOU OUT AND ABOUT
SO EARLY IN THE MORNING,
BUT WE NEVER REALLY
GET THE CHANCE TO TALK.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME IN,
HAVE A CUP OF TEA WITH ME?
- THANK YOU FOR THE OFFER, BUT
I SIMPLY DON'T HAVE TIME NOW.
HOWEVER, I WOULD BE HAPPY
TO JOIN YOU IN THE FUTURE.
- IF YOU SAY SO.
- ARE YOU TRYING TO PERSUADE HER
TO COME IN FOR TEA AGAIN?
COME ON, MOM,
I BET SHE'D LOVE TO,
BUT SHE'S A VERY BUSY LADY.
- RIGHT.
- WELL, I HAVE TO GO BY KONOE'S
TO WALK HER TO SCHOOL.
SEE YOU LATER.
- I HOPE YOU HAVE A GOOD DAY
AT SCHOOL, YUJI.
- PARDON, BUT I SHOULD BE
GOING AS WELL.
- I'M SORRY I COULDN'T
CHANGE YOUR MIND.
- ( knocks )
- GREETINGS, MASTER SAKAI.
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I AM AFRAID MISS KONOE
IS TAKING HER TIME
GETTING READY THIS MORNING.
I SINCERELY APOLOGIZE.
I HOPE YOU WON'T BE LATE
FOR CLASS.
I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH
FOR YOUR HELP.
- NO, FORGET IT.
- WELL, I SHOULD IMAGINE
THAT SHE'LL BE READY TO GO
ANY MOMENT NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU COME
AND WAIT FOR HER INSIDE?
- OH, I DON'T WANT
TO INTRUDE.
- NONSENSE, YOUNG MAN.
PLEASE COME IN.
THIS WAY,
MASTER SAKAI.
NORMALLY I WOULD BE
RESPONSIBLE
FOR WALKING HER TO SCHOOL
EACH AND EVERY DAY.
AGAIN, I'M SO GRATEFUL
FOR YOUR HELP.
IT ALLOWS ME TO GET MORE DONE
AROUND THE HOUSE.
- OH, HEY,
NO PROBLEM AT ALL, SIR.
I'M UP EARLY EVERY MORNING
FOR TRAINING ANYWAY,
SO IT'S NOT LIKE
IT'S AN INCONVENIENCE.
- AH, TRAINING, YOU SAY?
MAY I ASK FOR WHAT?
- UH, NOTHING BIG.  I'M JUST
TRYING TO GET A LITTLE STRONGER.
- GOOD MORNING, SAKAI.
( giggles )
- YOUR HOUSE IS ABSOLUTELY
AMAZING, KONOE.
IT'S NOT ONLY GORGEOUS
ON THE OUTSIDE,
BUT THE INSIDE TOO.
- IT'S JUST A NORMAL HOUSE.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
I FORGET SOMETIMES
THAT "NORMAL" FOR YOU IS
LIVING IN THE LAP OF LUXURY.
IN FACT, I'M BETTING
YOU WOULDN'T BE
EVEN A LITTLE IMPRESSED
WITH SATO'S FANCY PLACE.
- WHO IS SATO?
- HE'S A GUY
IN OUR CLASS.
HE WENT TO THE SUPERSIZE
RESTAURANT WITH US, REMEMBER?
- UH...
- IT'S OKAY.
TAKES TIME TO LEARN
EVERYONE'S NAMES.
- MAYBE SO,
BUT I HAVE NO PROBLEM
REMEMBERING YOUR NAME, SAKAI.
- I'M GLAD.
BUT YOU DO SPEND
MORE TIME WITH ME.
- OKAY, THIS IS
FOR CONTEMPORARY LIT.
AND HERE'S YOUR NOTEBOOK.
GREAT, YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO DO IT ON YOUR OWN NOW.
RIGHT?
THINK SO, YOSHIDA?
- UH, YEAH, SURE.
- I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN DO
ALL OF THIS BY MYSELF JUST YET.
- WHA--?  SERIOUSLY?
WELL, THERE'S NO NEED FOR YOU
TO PUSH YOURSELF.
JUST ASK ME IF YOU HAVE ANY
TROUBLE FIGURING IT OUT, OKAY?
- AH, SAKAI,
YOU'RE STILL HELPING KONOE.
- Students: GOOD MORNING.
- HAVING TO TAKE ON ALL THAT
RESPONSIBILITY IS PRETTY TOUGH,
DON'T YOU THINK?
POOR GUY, I HEAR
YOU'VE BEEN STUCK WITH HER
FROM MORNING TO NIGHT.
- I GUESS YOU COULD SAY THAT.
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOSHIDA'S BEEN HELPING ME
WITH HER TOO.
- ABOUT THAT: I DON'T THINK
SHE SHOULD HAVE TO.
I THINK IT'S GREAT THAT YOU
HELP HER HERE ON CAMPUS,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WALK WITH HER
TO AND FROM SCHOOL
EVERY DAY.
YOU LIVE IN THE OPPOSITE
DIRECTION
OF KONOE'S HOUSE,
DON'T YOU?
- UH, WELL, YEAH.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE I DIDN'T
THINK ABOUT THAT BEFORE.
MY APOLOGIES.
MM, LET'S SEE.
OGATA, YOU LIVE NEAR KONOE,
DON'T YOU?
DO YOU MIND TAKING OVER
YOSHIDA'S DUTIES?
- NO, I DON'T MIND.
I WOULD LOVE TO HELP HER OUT.
- OKAY THEN, LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK.
- YES, SIR.
- SO, JUST TO REITERATE,
STARTING THIS AFTERNOON
OGATA IS ON KONOE DUTY
WITH SAKAI.
NOW I EXPECT THE REST OF YOU
TO HELP THEM WITH HER
HERE AT SCHOOL.  GOT IT?
- YES, SIR.
- OH MY.
IT'S AN OFFER
I CANNOT REFUSE.
- Tiamat: IT IS
QUITE A MARKDOWN.
- WHAT'S GOING ON,
SAKAI?
WHERE THE HECK HAVE YOSHIDA AND
SHANA BEEN THE LAST FEW DAYS?
WHAT, THEY DON'T WANT
TO EAT LUNCH WITH US?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH THOSE TWO.
THEY'RE PROBABLY
JUST TRYING
TO WORK OUT THEIR
DIFFERENCES OR SOMETHING.
- DOUBT IT.  THAT'S NOT
THE VIBE I WAS GETTING.
- LOOK, SAKAI,
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT YOU THINK THEY MAY BE
UPSET WITH YOU?
THEY BOTH MAKE YOU
BOXED LUNCHES EVERY DAY.
MAYBE THEY THINK
YOU'RE NOT GRATEFUL.
- HMM.
- UM, SAKAI,
WOULD YOU MIND
IF I HAVE A LITTLE TASTE
OF EACH OF YOUR LUNCHES?
- NOT AT ALL.
GO AHEAD.
- YOU THINK I'M SPENDING
TOO MUCH TIME WITH KONOE?
YOU'VE SEEN
HOW HELPLESS SHE IS.
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN LEAVE HER
TO HER OWN DEVICES, YOU KNOW.
- I THINK YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT HERE, BUDDY.
YOU DON'T SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON AROUND YOU.
JUST TRY NOT TO SPEND
SO MUCH TIME WITH HER.
- THAT'S WEIRD.
- GATHER 'ROUND,
EVERYBODY!
I'VE GOT THE FRESHEST VEGETABLES
YOU'VE EVER SEEN--
CABBAGE, GREEN PEPPERS--
WHATEVER YOU LIKE.
WELCOME, YOUNG LADY.
WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU?
I GOT THE BEST PRICES
IN TOWN
AND THE FRESHEST PRODUCE,
GUARANTEED.
HEY, YOU'RE CHECKING OUT
THE CABBAGE, HUH?
GOOD CHOICE.  YOU CAN BOIL IT,
STIR-FRY IT OR SERVE IT RAW.
AND WITH A LITTLE
ELBOW GREASE,
THAT BAD BOY'LL MAKE
SOME MEAN CABBAGE ROLLS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT:
YOU'RE SUCH A LOOKER,
I'LL CUT YOU A DEAL.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- CABBAGE.
- Chigusa: WELL, HELLO THERE.
I DIDN'T EXPECT
TO RUN INTO YOU HERE.
- Seller: HERE YOU GO,
YOUNG LADY.
THANKS FOR YOUR PATRONAGE.
- OH, HELLO.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG,
WILHELMINA?
YOU SEEM LIKE YOU'RE
A LITTLE DOWN TODAY.
- NO, EVERYTHING IS FINE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR ASKING.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
I DON'T MEAN TO MEDDLE,
BUT ARE YOU HAVING
PROBLEMS WITH SHANA?
I KNOW IT'S NOT REALLY
MY PLACE,
BUT I NOTICED SHE HASN'T
COME TO VISIT IN A WHILE.
AND WHEN I ASK YUJI
ABOUT IT,
HE SEEMS CONFUSED
ABOUT THE WHOLE SITUATION.
- MA'AM,
I AM CURIOUS
ABOUT SOMETHING.
IS PRACTICALITY NOT ENOUGH WHEN
IT COMES TO PREPARING DINNER?
- PRACTICAL IS FINE.
BUT IF THAT WERE THE ONLY
REASON WE WERE TO COOK,
THEN WE WOULDN'T HAVE
HALF AS MUCH VARIETY.
- SO IT'S NOT SIMPLY
ABOUT GAINING NUTRITION.
IT'S ABOUT EXPERIENCING
VARIETY AS WELL?
- THAT'S RIGHT.  THERE'S AN ART
TO USING DIFFERENT INGREDIENTS
TO CREATE NEW AND EXCITING
FLAVOR COMBINATIONS
THAT MAKE EACH MEAL
AN EXPERIENCE ALL ITS OWN.
SO, WILHELMINA.
- YES, MA'AM?
- HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO COME BY
AND HAVE THAT CUP OF TEA
WE TALKED ABOUT?
- WHAT'S UP, OGATA?
YOU WANT TO HANG OUT
THIS AFTERNOON?
YOU DON'T HAVE PRACTICE,
DO YOU?
- SORRY, TANAKA,
BUT I CAN'T TODAY.
- BUT WHY NOT?
- YOU READY, OGATA?
WE'D BETTER GET A MOVE ON.
- YEAH, SURE.
BE RIGHT THERE.
I'VE BEEN PUT ON KONOE DUTY,
SO I'VE GOT TO HELP SAKAI.
I HAVE TO WALK HOME WITH THEM ON
THE DAYS I DON'T HAVE PRACTICE.
- OH, UM, OKAY THEN.
- SEE YA.
- SUCKS TO BE YOU.
- YEAH.
- Kazumi: WHY HAVEN'T YOU
GONE HOME YET?
- I COULD ASK YOU
THE SAME.
- Kazumi: THERE IT IS AGAIN.
I WISH THIS FEELING
WOULD JUST GO AWAY.
I-- I DON'T LIKE IT AT ALL.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T MEAN TO GET ANGRY,
BUT WHEN I SEE THEM
TOGETHER--
I DON'T KNOW WHY
IT GETS ON MY NERVES SO BAD.
- ( Margery moaning )
OH, YEAH!
THERE YOU GO.
OH, RIGHT THERE.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
YOU'VE GOT GREAT HANDS, SATO.
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW TO MAKE
A GIRL FEEL GOOD.
- CAN I STOP NOW,
MARGERY?
PLEASE, MY HANDS
ARE KILLING ME.
- HUH?  WE NEED TO WORK
ON YOUR STAMINA.
COME ON, KEEP IT UP
UNTIL I FINISH THIS GLASS.
- BUT THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID
FOR THE LAST THREE GLASSES.
JEEZ, HOW ARE YOUR
SHOULDERS STIFF
WHEN YOU JUST
SIT AROUND ALL DAY?
- ( Marcosias laughs )
SHE GOT YOU THERE, KIDDO.
SHE AIN'T STIFF.
SHE JUST DIGS MASSAGES.
- I'M AFRAID HE'S RIGHT.
IF YOU'RE TOO TIRED TO CONTINUE,
WHY DON'T YOU MAKE EITA
TAKE OVER FOR YA?
- WELL, I WOULD,
BUT HE'S NOT HERE YET.
- WHAT?
WHERE IS HE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I BET YOU HE RAN AWAY.
MUST HAVE WISED UP AND REALIZED
THE GIG'S NOT FOR HIM.
I MEAN, IF YOU WANT TO HANG
WITH MARGERY DAW,
YOU BETTER HAVE STRONG HANDS
AND SOME SERIOUS PATIENCE.
THAT GIRL CAN BE QUITE A HANDFUL
WHEN SHE'S DRUNK,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GETTING AT.
- STUPID MARCO, SHUT UP.
- CUT IT OUT
WITH THE THROWING!
- I'M SURPRISED KONOE'S FAMILY
BOUGHT THAT MANSION.
NO ONE'S LIVED THERE IN YEARS.
IT'S SUCH AN OLD PLACE,
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO GO TO
RUIN, BUT I GUESS IT WON'T NOW.
- THAT'S INTERESTING.
HER BUTLER INVITED ME INSIDE
THIS MORNING,
AND THE PLACE DIDN'T LOOK
LIKE IT WAS VERY OLD AT ALL.
I DID NOTICE THERE WERE
A LOT OF EMPTY ROOMS THOUGH.
- WELL, IT MAKES SENSE.
KONOE AND HER BUTLER ARE THE
ONLY ONES LIVING THERE, RIGHT?
OBVIOUSLY THEY CAN'T OCCUPY ALL
THE ROOMS IN THAT HUGE PLACE.
- YEAH, I GUESS
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT STILL, THERE WAS SOMETHING
STRANGE ABOUT IT.
- HMM.
- OH, HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ARE YOU GUYS HEADED BACK
FROM KONOE'S HOUSE?
- ARE YOU HERE 'CAUSE YOU WERE
WORRIED ABOUT ME?
- NO, DON'T BE SILLY.
I JUST HAPPENED
TO BE PASSING BY.
- SO ARE YOU GOING OVER
TO SATO'S PLACE TO HANG OUT?
- UM, NO, NOT TODAY.
- Alastor: WH-- WHAT'S HAPPENED?
- WILHELMINA!
WHERE ARE YOU, WILHELMINA?
HELLO?
WILHELMINA, ANSWER ME!
ARE YOU--?
- WELCOME HOME, MILADY.
YOUR DINNER SHOULD BE
READY TO SERVE
IN JUST A FEW MORE
MINUTES.
- MY DINNER?
- Alastor: YOU COOKED IT
YOURSELF?
OF COURSE.  I'VE USED
DIFFERENT INGREDIENTS
TO CREATE NEW AND EXCITING
FLAVOR COMBINATIONS.
- Tiamat: VARIETY IS
THE SPICE OF LIFE.
- PLEASE DO NOT BE AFRAID.
I HAVE TRAINED LONG AND HARD
TO ACCOMPLISH THIS FEAT.
- Alastor: SEEMS HER TRAINING
DIDN'T COVER
TURNING THE VENTILATION
FANS ON.
- Yuji: HEY, MOM.
- WELCOME HOME, SWEETHEART.
I'M IN THE KITCHEN.
- WHAT THE--?  WHAT ON EARTH
HAPPENED IN HERE?
- ( chuckles )
GUESS I MADE
A BIT OF A MESS, HUH?
- I'D CALL THAT
MORE THAN A BIT.
- I APOLOGIZE
FOR THE WAIT, MILADY.
- Alastor: EXCUSE ME,
WILHELMINA,
BUT WOULD YOU
PLEASE TELL US
WHAT THIS INTERESTING-LOOKING
DISH IS CALLED?
- IT IS A CABBAGE ROLL.
- THAT'S A CABBAGE ROLL?
- INDEED.  I HAD TO
CUT THE CABBAGE,
COOK THE MEAT, ADD THE SEASONING
AND LET IT STEW.
I'VE ENSURED THIS MEAL IS
NOT ONLY FULL OF MUCH NEEDED
NUTRITIONAL VALUE,
BUT ALSO TASTES GOOD.
- Tiamat: AN IMPROVED EPICUREAN.
- Alastor: A BIASED OPINION.
- I THOUGHT A HOME-COOKED MEAL
MIGHT HELP CHEER YOU UP.
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK,
MILADY?
- KIND OF BITTER.
AND IT COULD PROBABLY
USE SOME SALT.
BUT YOU TOOK THE TIME
TO MAKE IT FOR ME,
SO I LOVE IT.
THANKS A LOT.
- SHANA'S STILL ANGRY WITH ME
FOR SOME REASON.
MAYBE WE'LL GET A CHANCE
TO TALK ABOUT IT TOMORROW.
I THINK
IKE'S GOT A POINT.
I NEED TO BE
MORE AWARE.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: SATO AGREES
TO HOLD AN ALL-NIGHT
STUDY SESSION AT HIS PLACE, AND
THE WHOLE GANG'S GONNA BE THERE.
THINGS MAY GET A BIT AWKWARD,
BECAUSE SHANA AND YOSHIDA
HAVE BEEN KIND OF WEIRD
AROUND ME LATELY.
AND THEN THERE'S
WHATEVER THAT IS GOING ON
WITH OGATA AND TANAKA.
MARGERY SENSES
THAT SOMETHING IS AWRY
AND DECIDES TO GIVE THE GIRLS
SOME SAGE ADVICE.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"EVE OF TROUBLE".