- Announcer:
DURING THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL,
MISAKI HIGH WAS ATTACKED BY
PHELES, THE CAPRICE OF BEAUTY,
WHO WAS DETERMINED
TO FREE HER ETERNAL LOVER
FROM THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
YUJI THEN CAST A SEAL,
AND MARGERY WENT BERSERK
UPON SEEING ITS COLOR.
EVERYONE INVOLVED IS
TOUCHED BY SORROW.
AS THEY FIND THEMSELVES
WONDERING WHAT THE FUTURE HOLDS.
- ( theme music playing )
- THE MIDGET'S LATE.
THERE'S ONLY 30 MINUTES
UNTIL YOUR POWER
OF EXISTENCE
IS REPLENISHED.
WELL, IF SHE DOESN'T
SHOW UP SOON,
I SUPPOSE I'LL JUST
HAVE TO MAKE DO.
- COOL YOUR JETS,
MARGERY DAW.
THE KID'S GOT
PLENTY OF TIME.
THE FLAMING-HAIRED,
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER
STILL HAS HALF AN HOUR
BEFORE IT'S MIDNIGHT.
- SHE MUST NOT BE TOO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU, HUH?
WHY ELSE WOULD
SHE LEAVE YOU HERE UNATTENDED?
THE CAPRICE OF BEAUTY
AND I COULD TEAR YOU APART.
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
- THAT'S TRUE.
SHE PROMISED SHANA
SHE WOULDN'T TOUCH ME,
BUT BECAUSE OF MY SILVER FLAME,
I'M STILL HER ENEMY.
AND THEN THERE'S HER.
PHELES.  SHE'D RIP ME
TO SHREDS TO FREE JOHAN
FROM THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- WHAT'S UP?
YOU GETTING COLD FEET?
A LITTLE.
- WELL, I CAN'T REALLY
SAY I BLAME YOU
WITH WHAT YOU'RE
FACING RIGHT NOW.
WHAT'S TAKING HER SO LONG?
SHANA.
- SAKAI.
- SHARE YUJI'S POWER
OF EXISTENCE?
- HE WILL HAVE PLENTY TO SPARE
WHEN HIS IS RESTORED
AT MIDNIGHT.
SHE DOESN'T NEED MUCH.
JUST ENOUGH TO STAND AND TALK.
- Alastor: HMM.
SHE WON'T BE OF ANY HELP TO US
IN HER PRESENT CONDITION.
IT MUST BE DONE IF YOU WANT
TO QUESTION HER FURTHER.
- BUT, ALASTOR.
SHE'S OUT TO GET YUJI.
- MISTRESS, PLEASE, DON'T WORRY.
I SWEAR.  I WILL PROTECT
THE MYSTES MYSELF.
I SHALL STAY BY HIS SIDE
AND KEEP A CLOSE EYE ON PHELES.
PERHAPS IF WE OBSERVE
HOW THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
REACTS TO ITS CREATOR,
IT COULD
TELL US SOMETHING ABOUT--
- AH.  YOU THINK IT MIGHT
TELL US SOMETHING
ABOUT THE SILVER.
- ARE YOU IN?
- OF COURSE I'LL DO IT.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY, RIGHT?
- OKAY.  BUT YOU HAVE TO PROMISE
YOU WON'T TOUCH HIM.
OR THE DEAL IS OFF.
- CAN YOU AGREE TO THAT, PHELES?
YOU MUST PROMISE NOT
TO DESTROY THE MYSTES
IF YOU WISH TO BE REUNITED
WITH JOHAN.
- ( sighs )
- I NEED YOU TO AGREE TO THIS
BEFORE WE CAN MOVE FORWARD.
- I PROMISE.
FOR MY LOVE JOHAN.
- ( sighs )
- WE SHALL MEET AT MIDNIGHT,
THE QUESTION IS WHERE.
- HOW ABOUT KEISAKU'S PLACE?
THEN I WON'T HAVE TO DEAL
WITH CASTING A SEAL.
- WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- WELL, I--
- THIS IS NO PLACE
FOR AN ORDINARY HUMAN.
- I'M JUST A REGULAR PERSON.
I DON'T BELONG IN SHANA
AND SAKAI'S WORLD.
DO I?
- ( knock on door )
- WHO'S THERE?
- Shana: ARE YOU COMING?
- BUT I THOUGHT I WASN'T--
- JUST GET DRESSED.
HURRY IT UP.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
Shana: NOBODY'S AWAKE.
IF THEY WERE,
I'D HAVE SENSED IT.
- ( sighs )
YOU CAN SENSE THAT?
IS IT BECAUSE YOU'VE
SPENT SO MUCH TIME
WITH A HUMAN LIKE SAKAI?
- DO YOU WANT TO GO OR NOT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I WANNA SUPPORT SAKAI.
- IF THAT'S WHAT YOUR HEART
IS TELLING YOU TO DO, KAZUMI.
WHO CARES WHAT PHELES SAID?
IT SHOULDN'T MATTER TO YOU.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- LET'S GO.
DON'T LET ANYTHING THE CAPRICE
OF BEAUTY SAYS AFFECT YOU, OKAY?
- THIS IS AMAZING.
THE WORLD OF THE FLAME HAZE.
BUT I WONDER.
WHY IS SHE SHARING THIS
WITH ME?
HER EXPRESSION.
I'VE SEEN THAT EXPRESSION
BEFORE.
- I'LL TELL HIM.
I WILL.
I'LL TELL YUJI HOW I FEEL.
- I WON'T GIVE UP.
- AND NEITHER WILL I.
- WHAT?
- JUST A LITTLE SURPRISED.
- ALL RIGHTY THEN.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT
EVERYONE WE NEED PRESENT.
AND WE EVEN HAVE
A SPECIAL GUEST.
ARE YOU READY?
WE'D BETTER GET STARTED.
- WHY'D SHANA BRING YOSHIDA?
- CALM DOWN, KIDDO.
I CAST A FEW UNRESTRICTED
SPELLS TO OBSERVE.
- Marcosias: ( laughs )
"A FEW"?  I COUNT FIVE OF 'EM.
YOU SURE ARE BEING THOROUGH.
NICE TO SEE YOU EXERCISE
SOME CAUTION FOR ONCE.
- WATCH IT.
I'M WARNING YOU RIGHT NOW.
IF YOU TOUCH HIS CORE,
I'LL KILL YOU.
- DON'T PANIC.  SHE HASN'T
THREATENED THE MYSTES.
- Tiamat:
JUST AN EMBRACE.
- JOHAN.
I FINALLY FOUND YOU.
YOU'RE SO CLOSE AND YET.
- YUJI!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
I KEPT MY PROMISE.
I DIDN'T TOUCH ITS CORE.
- THE TRANSFER OF POWER
OF EXISTENCE
HAS INDEED BEEN COMPLETED.
IT'S OVER.
- YOU'RE NOT HURT, ARE YOU?
- I'M FINE.
- DID YOU
FIND ANYTHING WORTH MENTION?
- ( laughs )
WELL, IT APPEARS
THAT THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
HAS BEEN AFFECTED BY A SPELL.
- IT MUST BE SABRAC'S SPELL.
- I COULDN'T SAY WHETHER
IT WAS HIS OR NOT.
BUT IT HAS MUTATED THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD'S KEEPER.
- BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW COULD IT?
- NOT SURE.  THE ONLY WAY
TO FIND OUT IS
TO INSPECT THE TREASURE TOOL
IN PERSON.
HOWEVER, I WOULDN'T RISK
REMOVING IT
FROM THE MYSTES WITHOUT KNOWING
WHAT DANGER
MAY BE LURKING INSIDE.
- IS THERE A CONNECTION BETWEEN
THE SPELL AND THE SILVER?
- POSSIBLY,
BUT I WASN'T ABLE
TO FIND ONE AT THIS TIME.
( sighs )
THE SPELLS I CAST
DIDN'T REALLY GIVE ME
ANY CLEAR ANSWERS.
THEY JUST LEFT ME
WITH MORE QUESTIONS.
- ( Marcosias laughing )
YOU'RE TELLING ME JOHAN,
THE SILVER AND SOME OTHER SPELL
ARE ALL HANGING OUT
IN THERE?
THIS MYSTES, TORCH OR WHATEVER
YOU WANNA CALL IT,
IT'S A PANDORA'S BOX
IF YOU ASK ME.
- WHO CARES WHETHER
HE'S A TORCH OR A MYSTES?
- HE'S STILL SAKAI.
- YOSHIDA.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
- I'M JUST AN ORDINARY HUMAN.
I MAY NOT MATTER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE A FLAME HAZE
OR A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE CRIMSON WORLD,
BUT PLEASE DO SOMETHING
FOR ME, PHELES.
- STEP RIGHT UP,
LADIES AND GENTS.
ODEN'S ALWAYS BETTER
ON THE SECOND DAY.
- Boy: HEY, IS THAT...
- Boy #2: YEP, THE GRAND PRIZE
WINNER AND RUNNER-UP.
- Girl:
WHO'S THAT WITH THEM?
SHE'S GORGEOUS.
- Wilhelmina: IT IS SAID
THAT YESTERDAY'S ENEMY
IS TOMORROW'S FRIEND.
HOWEVER, I NEVER IMAGINED
THEY WOULD TAKE
THAT PROVERB LITERALLY.
- Tiamat: AGREED.
- I'M SHOCKED.
WHO KNEW KAZUMI YOSHIDA
HAD SUCH COURAGE WITHIN HER?
- SURPRISING.
- PLEASE DO SOMETHING
FOR ME, PHELES.
COME TO THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL
WITH ME.
- WAIT, WHAT?
- KAZUMI.
- AW, JEEZ.  THIS HAS GOTTA
BE SOME KIND OF JOKE.
YOU DO KNOW WHO SHE IS,
DON'T YOU?
- OF COURSE I DO.
SHE'S A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
BUT SHE'S MORE THAN THAT.
SHE'S A WOMAN WHO'S
IN LOVE WITH A MAN.
WE HAVE THAT IN COMMON.
WE ALL FALL IN LOVE.
HUMANS AND DENIZENS ALIKE.
THE MYSTES YOU WANTED
TO DESTROY.
HE'S SPECIAL.
SO PLEASE COME, PHELES.
I WANT FOR YOU TO SEE HOW
IMPORTANT SAKAI IS TO ME.
- I'LL GO TO THE FESTIVAL
WITH YOU, TOO.
- SHANA.
- FOR YUJI'S PROTECTION,
OF COURSE.
I'M NOT READY TO LET PHELES
OUT OF MY SIGHT JUST YET.
- YOSHIDA SEEMS
SO MUCH STRONGER NOW.
AND I NOTICED SHANA
CALLED HER "KAZUMI."
I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN THEM?
HEY, IS THERE A REASON WE HAVE
TO HANG OUT UP HERE ON OUR OWN?
- IT'S BEST WE KEEP
YOU TWO SEPARATED.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS FOR YOU
TO ATTEND THE FESTIVAL
WHILE PHELES IS THERE.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR VERY
EXISTENCE IS IN DANGER.
YES?
- Tiamat: BLUBBERING IDIOT.
- HERE.
I BROUGHT YOU BOTH A CREPE.
OUR CLASS IS RUNNING A STAND.
TRY IT.
IT'S REALLY GOOD.
UH... SO IS THIS
YOUR FIRST FESTIVAL?
I GUESS I SHOULD EXPLAIN.  IT'S
LIKE A BIG PARTY ORGANIZED BY--
- I KNOW WHAT A FESTIVAL IS,
THANK YOU.
JOHAN WOULD TAKE ME TO THEM.
- I'M BREAKING THROUGH
TO HER.
I'M SURE SHE'LL
LEAVE SAKAI ALONE
ONCE SHE SEES
HOW I FEEL ABOUT HIM.
- I HAVE A HARD TIME BELIEVING
PHELES IS GOING TO OPEN
HER HEART TO US, BUT MAYBE
KAZUMI IS ON TO SOMETHING.
- SO WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO NEXT?
- WELL, I'M STUFFED
SO NO MORE FOOD, OKAY?
- LET ME SEE.  THERE'S
THE MARKET OR THE ARCADE.
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
IT'S MY TREAT.
- LOOK WHO'S HERE.
- HEY, GUYS.
- OH, HEY.
- HAVING A GOOD TIME, MATAKE?
- YEAH. ( laughs )
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- BIG LUG,
GOT YOUR LADY ALL WORRIED.
PICK THAT CHIN UP, YOUNG MAN.
- COME ON, LET'S GO.
- EITA, YOU DON'T HAVE TO RUSH.
YOU'VE GOT PLENTY OF TIME,
MY FRIEND.
THE MEMORY THAT HAUNTS YOU,
IT WASN'T BASED IN REALITY.
PLEASE,
TRY TO KEEP THAT IN MIND.
- YEAH.
- HEY, WAIT.
- MARGERY.
WHAT HE WITNESSED,
IT MUST'VE BEEN HARD.
I'M SURE IT SCARED HIM
HALF TO DEATH.
I'M HOPING
HE'LL USE THE EXPERIENCE
TO LEARN MORE ABOUT HIMSELF
AND WHAT'S IMPORTANT TO HIM.
- ( laughs )
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU THINK
YOU CAN PLAY PSYCHOLOGIST
WHEN YOU'RE THE ONE WHO MESSED
THE KID UP IN THE FIRST PLACE.
YOU GOT SOME NERVE,
MARGERY-- OW!
- SHUT UP, STUPID MARCO.
- YOU LOOK TROUBLED, INDEED.
- NO, I WAS JUST THINKING.
THIS IS THE PERFECT PLACE
FOR ME.
EVERYONE ELSE IS OUT HAVING
A GOOD TIME.
WHILE MY TIME ON THE OTHER HAND
IS PRACTICALLY FROZEN.
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
IS THE ONLY THING
THAT KEEPS IT TICKING.
TELL ME ABOUT JOHAN.
HE'S INSIDE THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD
AND HE WAS A MYSTES.
JUST LIKE ME.  WAS HE A--
- THAT'S RIGHT.
HE WAS ONCE HUMAN.
BUT UNLIKE YOU,
HE CHOSE TO BE A MYSTES.
PHELES HAS ALWAYS BEEN A STRONG
YET WHIMSICAL DENIZEN.
SHE ALWAYS INSISTED ON
LIVING IN THE MOMENT.
SHE RESCUED JOHAN
FROM HIS FATHER,
WHO WANTED TO SACRIFICE HIM
TO GAIN ETERNAL LIFE.
SHE CHOSE TO RAISE THE CHILD
AND AS HE GREW,
THEY GREW CLOSER.
UNTIL ONE DAY.
JUST AS YOSHIDA SAID,
"WE ALL FALL IN LOVE,
HUMANS AND DENIZENS ALIKE."
I'M SURE PHELES
ACCEPTED HER INVITATION
BECAUSE SHE AGREED
WITH THAT SENTIMENT.
- ( sighs ) ALMOST THERE.
THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL
IS ALMOST OVER.
AND THEN I'LL BE ABLE TO REST.
- IKE, I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR YOU.
ANOTHER CHILD IS MISSING.
COME QUICKLY.
- ( screams )
- IS THE FESTIVAL ENDING?
JOHAN WILL BE UPSET.
- PHELES.
- SAD, ISN'T IT?
ANOTHER FESTIVAL OVER.
- ALL THINGS COME TO AN END.
PLEASE, DON'T BE UPSET.
TO CHEER YOU UP,
I'LL GIVE YOU ANYTHING
YOUR HEART DESIRES, JOHAN.
- ANYTHING AT ALL?
YOU MEAN IT?
- OF COURSE.
- MY HEART DESIRES YOU.
TO BE WITH YOU
FOR ALL OF ETERNITY.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
I WOULD GLADLY
GIVE UP MY HUMANITY
IF-- IF IT MEANT I COULD BE
WITH YOU FOREVER.
- YOU WOULD?
- ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS TRICK TIME.
WE'LL MAKE IT STOP
AT MIDNIGHT.
- NO, JOHAN.  YOU MUSTN'T.
- TELL ME YOU WANT TO SPEND
ALL OF ETERNITY WITH ME.
- I DO.
- THEN I SHALL BECOME A MYSTES.
I SHALL STOP TIME
SO I MAY STAY BY YOUR SIDE,
MY BELOVED PHELES.
- JOHAN.
- YOU'RE CRYING.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- IT'S NOTHING.
I WAS JUST REMINISCING.
I ONCE
HAD A LOVE MUCH LIKE YOURS.
YOU MUST TREASURE
YOUR TIME TOGETHER.
- FINALLY SHE UNDERSTANDS.
- ( bell rings )
- THIS CONCLUDES THE 72ND ANNUAL
MISAKI HIGH SCHOOL
AUTUMN FESTIVAL.
JOIN US AGAIN NEXT YEAR.
IT'S SURE TO BE A BLAST.
- ( cheering )
- THANK YOU, WILHELMINA.
I WAS SO VERY FORTUNATE
TO RECONNECT WITH AN OLD FRIEND
LIKE YOU IN THIS PLACE.
THANKS TO YOU,
I'M STILL STANDING
AND I KNOW WHAT JOHAN
IS FACING.
I SIMPLY CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
- PHELES.
- Tiamat: SO JUBILANT.
- I OWE MY GRATITUDE TO YOU,
AS WELL,
CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
IF YOU HAD NOT WARNED ME
ABOUT THE KEEPER'S MUTATION,
I MIGHT HAVE UNLEASHED
SOMETHING TREACHEROUS
FROM WITHIN THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD.
- I ONLY HELPED YOU TO SAVE
MY OWN HIDE, GOT IT?
- ALSO SHANA,
FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
AND, KAZUMI, WHAT YOU
SHARED WITH ME WAS SO SPECIAL.
YOU GAVE ME THE GIFT
OF YOUR TIME.
AND I AM SO VERY GRATEFUL
FOR IT.
THANK YOU.
- FOR WHAT?
- THANKS TO YOU
THE REAL ME IS READY
TO REUNITE WITH JOHAN.
- ( gasps )
- NO!
- SAKAI!
- THAT PRESENCE.
- FIGURES.
- NO.
- Shana: PHELES!
- I SEE.
WE HAVEN'T BEEN DEALING WITH THE
REAL PHELES, JUST A PLACEHOLDER.
IT WAS MERELY A FRAGMENT
OF HER CONSCIOUSNESS.
- SO THIS ONE
IS THE REAL THING?
- SHE WAS USING
AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL.
THE WHEEL OF WIND.
IT CREATES A DOPPELGANGER
THAT ACTS AS A HOMING DEVICE.
AN ANCHOR TO LEAD
THE CASTER HERE, BUT WHY?
- YOU COULDN'T HAVE MADE THIS
ANY MORE CONVENIENT FOR ME.
JUST LOOK AT THIS LINEUP.
AN OLD FRIEND,
AN OBSESSED SPELL CASTER,
A HUNTER IN LOVE
AND A FOOLISH LITTLE GIRL.
I MANIPULATED
EVERY LAST ONE OF YOU
TO BE REUNITED WITH MY JOHAN.
- PHELES, NO.
SINCE IT'S TOO DANGEROUS
TO REACH INSIDE OF YOU.
I'LL HAVE HIM COME OUT
ON HIS OWN.
I'M HERE, JOHAN.
- ( screaming )
- YUJI!
- ( slashing )
- ( gasps )
JOHAN.
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji: A SILVER HAND CLAD IN
ARMOR SUDDENLY REACHES OUT
FROM WITHIN THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD, IMPALING PHELES.
BEFORE WE CAN EVEN FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S HAPPENING,
THINGS TAKE A TURN
FOR THE WORSE.
WE LEARN THAT OUR NEWEST
FRIEND, FUMINA KONOE,
ACTUALLY HAS BEEN
KEEPING A SECRET.
NEXT TIME ON
"SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND"...
"AWAKENING."