- Alastor:
YUJI REVEALED THE SECRET
OF THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE
SABRAC'S SEEMING
INVINCIBILITY--
HE HAD SPREAD HIS POWER
THROUGHOUT MISAKI CITY.
SHANA, MARGERY, AND WILHELMINA
CARRIED OUT YUJI'S PLAN.
AND THE VILLAINOUS SABRAC
WAS FINALLY DEFEATED.
- ( theme music playing )
- GOOD WORK OUT THERE,
SABRAC.
- YOU DID NOT EXAGGERATE.
THEY ARE INDEED
A POWERFUL GROUP.
IN MY ATTEMPT TO GET MY HANDS
ON THE MYSTES,
I HAD HOPED TO EXTERMINATE
THE THREE FLAME HAZE.
AH, BUT PLANS RARELY WORK OUT
THE WAY WE'D LIKE.
- IT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
YOU ACCOMPLISHED
WHAT WE NEEDED FROM YOU.
THE REST IS UP TO US.
- MMM. IF MY SERVICES
ARE NO LONGER REQUIRED,
THEN I SEE NO REASON TO LINGER.
WITH YOUR PERMISSION,
I SHALL TAKE MY LEAVE.
- Bel-Peol:
NOW LET THE FUN BEGIN.
- HERE GOES.
( sighs )
- Marcosias ( laughing ):
THAT WAS SURE A HEAVY SIGH,
KIDDO.
- WHAT'S GOT YOU RILED UP
THIS MORNING?
- I'VE DECIDED--
I WANT TO WORK FOR OUTLAW.
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
I'LL USE ANY ADVANTAGE I HAVE.
EVEN IF IT MEANS
ASKING THINGS OF PEOPLE
I DON'T WANT TO DEPEND ON.
- Marcosias:
HE HATES HIS FATHER,
AND HE'S REACHING OUT
TO HIM FOR HELP?
IF HE'S WILLING TO DO THAT,
HE MUST BE SERIOUS.
I DON'T THINK
YOU CAN STOP HIM, MARGERY.
- SO MUCH FOR TRYING
TO SCARE HIM
INTO CHANGING HIS MIND.
- Marcosias: HMM, YEAH,
A WHOLE LOT OF GOOD THAT DID.
IF ANYTHING, YOU JUST
STRENGTHENED HIS RESOLVE.
- Sato:
I DON'T WANT TO THINK
ABOUT WHAT I WOULD DO
IF YOU WERE TO DIE.
- HE REALLY IS AN IDIOT.
- EVERYONE SEEMS
TO HAVE CHANGED.
SATO AND TANAKA BARELY TALK
TO EACH OTHER ANYMORE.
SHANA AND YOSHIDA
ARE CHATTING LIKE BEST FRIENDS.
AND SAKAI--
I DON'T KNOW. HE DOESN'T
LOOK ANY DIFFERENT,
BUT HE SEEMS TO HAVE
CHANGED THE MOST.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
- IKE!
THE PREZ WANTS TO SEE US.
IT SHOULDN'T TAKE TOO LONG.
JUST A QUICK MEETING
BEFORE SCHOOL LETS OUT.
- OKAY.
GUESS I NEED A CHANGE TOO--
A BIG ONE.
- Boy: SEE YOU NEXT YEAR!
- Girl: ARE YOU GOING
TO THE NEW YEAR'S PARTY?
- THIS SEMESTER FLEW BY.
WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY?
- I'M GOING
TO SHOW MY REPORT CARD
TO YOUR MOTHER
AND THEN I'M GOING
TO MEET UP WITH KAZUMI.
YOU'RE HANGING OUT?
- FOR A BIT, I GUESS.
- COOL.
- YO.
- DAD.
- ARE YOU SURE IT'S OKAY
FOR SHANA TO WALK HOME ALONE?
- YEAH, SHE'S HEADING
OVER TO VISIT MOM.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO TALK TO ME ABOUT SOMETHING?
- I DO.
THE RIVER LOOKS SO PEACEFUL
IN THE WINTER.
I'VE TRAVELED AROUND THE WORLD,
BUT THERE'S NO PLACE
LIKE MISAKI CITY.
IT ALWAYS FEELS LIKE HOME.
- Yuji: I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
CAN YOU STAY A WHILE
THIS TIME?
FOR NEW YEAR'S, AT LEAST?
- I REALLY WISH I COULD.
THIS WAS JUST A QUICK TRIP
'CAUSE OF AN URGENT CALL I GOT.
I HEAD BACK TOMORROW.
SUCKS.
- URGENT CALL?
FROM MOM?
- YEAH.
I MADE HER PROMISE TO CALL ME
WHENEVER SHE'S IN TROUBLE.
- WHAT-- IS SHE OKAY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
SHE KEEPS TELLING ME
THERE'S NO REASON TO WORRY,
BUT YOUR MOM'S
ALWAYS BEEN KIND OF CLUELESS
WHEN IT COMES TO HER HEALTH.
- HOLD ON, DAD.
WHAT KIND OF TROUBLE
IS SHE IN EXACTLY?
- DON'T GET ALL WORKED UP,
YUJI.
SHE JUST DIDN'T KNOW
HOW TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
- THAT'S FINE.
BUT I FEEL BAD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
MOM WAS SO UPSET
SHE THOUGHT HAD TO CALL YOU.
I NEVER EVEN REALIZED THAT--
- HMM.  IT'S OKAY.
NOT TO CHANGE THE SUBJECT,
BUT DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
HELP ME OUT WITH SOMETHING?
- I GUESS.
- WELL, I JUST CAN'T SEEM
TO COME UP
WITH A GOOD NAME
FOR YOUR NEW SIBLING.  CAN YOU?
- I'VE NEVER BEEN
VERY GOOD COMING UP WI--
HUH?!
UH, DID YOU JUST SAY,
"NEW SIBLING"?
- YEAH, I DID.
MOM'S PREGNANT.
- OH.
AWESOME.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WAIT A SEC.
THIS IS A GOOD THING,
ISN'T IT?
- IT IS.
CONGRATS TO YOU TOO,
BIG BROTHER.
- BROTHER.
HUH.
WHY WAS MOM SO WORRIED
ABOUT TELLING ME THAT?
- BECAUSE THERE'S A SECRET
THAT WE'VE BEEN
KEEPING FROM YOU.
- SECRET?
- WE DIDN'T THINK
WE'D EVER GET PREGNANT AGAIN.
OTHERWISE WE WOULD HAVE TOLD YOU
A LONG TIME AGO.
YOUR MOM WAS TOO NERVOUS
TO TELL YOU HERSELF.
SO I CAME BACK
TO LEND HER HAND.
AND HERE WE ARE.
- TELL ME.
I THINK I'M OLD ENOUGH
TO HANDLE IT.
- HMM.
THE REASON
WE GOT MARRIED SO YOUNG
IS BECAUSE YOUR MOM
GOT PREGNANT.
- WITH ME, RIGHT?
- THERE WERE COMPLICATIONS
DURING DELIVERY.
WHEN WE LOST THE BABY,
DOCTORS TOLD US
THAT WE'D NEVER
HAVE ANOTHER CHILD.
- BUT...
- THEY WERE WRONG.
IT TURNED OUT
TO BE A FALSE DIAGNOSIS.
IT TOOK A LITTLE WHILE,
BUT WE FINALLY
HAD A HEALTHY BABY BOY.
BASICALLY,
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS...
YOUR MOTHER AND I
HAVE BEEN BLESSED WITH TWO SONS.
- TWO?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
ONE SON WHO'S STANDING HERE
WITH ME NOW,
AND ANOTHER ONE
WHO DIDN'T SURVIVE--
YOUR BIG BROTHER.
WHEN WE WERE
CHOOSING A NAME FOR YOU,
WE WANTED TO FIND SOMETHING
THAT WOULD PAY HOMAGE
TO YOUR OLDER BROTHER
WHO HAD PASSED AWAY.
BUT IT ALSO HAD TO CONVEY
YOUR STRENGTH
AS THE SON WHO SURVIVED.
IF YOU ASK ME,
WE DID A PRETTY GOOD JOB.
THE NAME YUJI
MEANS COURAGEOUS SECOND SON.
IF I CAN FIND A NAME
THAT RELATES
TO THE NUMBER THREE,
I'D LIKE TO KEEP UP
THE TRADITION WITH THIS BABY.
MAY I?
- THANK YOU FOR SHARING
ALL THAT WITH ME, DAD.
- WELCOME HOME, GUYS.
- Yuji: I'VE GOT DAD AND MOM
AND NOW A NEW SIBLING
ON THE WAY.
NOW MORE THAN EVER
IT'S CLEAR TO ME,
I KNOW WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
IT'S MY DUTY
TO PROTECT THIS CITY
AND THE PEOPLE I LOVE.
- ( doorbell ringing )
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- I COULD REALLY
USE SOME ADVICE.
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- YOU REALIZE YOU'RE EARLY.
- YEAH, BUT YOU'VE
OBVIOUSLY BEEN HERE FOR A WHILE.
SOMETHING WRONG?
- CAN YOU, UH, TELL ME
WHERE BABIES COME FROM?
- WHY'RE YOU ASKING ME?
- OH, GREAT.
THAT SAME LOOK AGAIN.
WHY DOES EVERYONE
HAVE THAT FACE
WHEN I ASK 'EM THIS?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
HOW YOU GO ABOUT MAKING A BABY.
- I THINK
WE'LL NEED PERMISSION
FROM YOUR GUARDIANS
TO TELL YOU THAT.
RIGHT, DEAR?
- YES.
I'LL GIVE ALASTOR
AND WILHELMINA A CALL.
I THINK THAT'D
BE FOR THE BEST.
- HMM?
I ASKED ALASTOR.
- YOU DIDN'T TELL HER?
- Alastor:
PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME DO IT.
- CHIGUSA SAID SHE'D TALK TO ME
ABOUT IT LATER.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO WAIT.
I WANT TO KNOW NOW.
- SO I'M ASKING YOU
'CAUSE I FIGURED YOU'D TELL ME.
PLEASE, I REALLY WANT TO KNOW.
- UH, THING IS...
HAVING TO ANSWER THAT QUESTION
IS MORE EMBARRASSING
THAN BEING NAKED IN PUBLIC.
- NAKED IN PUBLIC?
- YEAH SO, UM...
- MMM.
- HOW COOL.
SAKAI'S GONNA BE
A BIG BROTHER.
- YEAH, HE'S EXCITED.
GOT TO SAY,
HE'S DEFINITELY COME A LONG WAY.
HE'S GOTTEN SO MUCH STRONGER,
AND NOT JUST IN TRAINING,
BUT OVERALL AS A PERSON.
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
YUJI AND I ARE NOT
GONNA BE LEAVING THE CITY.
BUT WE'LL HAVE TO CONTINUE
WITH HIS TRAINING.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHERE HE GOES,
HE'LL BE TARGETED
BECAUSE
OF THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- DOES SAKAI
KNOW HOW YOU FEEL?
- NO.
BUT I WILL TELL HIM
AND WE'LL SETTLE THIS.
TOMORROW IS DECEMBER THE 24th.
- IT'S CHRISTMAS EVE.
DO YOU HAVE A PLAN IN MIND?
- IF WE BOTH CONFRONT HIM
AT THE SAME TIME,
THEN IT'S JUST
GOING TO OVERWHELM HIM.
THAT'S WHY I SUGGEST
WE ASK HIM
TO MEET US
IN DIFFERENT PLACES.
AND WHOEVER YUJI
CHOOSES TO MEET
IS THE WINNER OF HIS HEART.
- BUT HOW ARE WE GONNA
EXPLAIN ALL OF THIS TO HIM?
- TO AVOID INFLUENCING HIM,
SO HE CAN
MAKE AN HONEST CHOICE,
I THINK IT'S BEST
IF WE BOTH WRITE HIM LETTERS.
- YOU MEAN
LIKE LOVE LETTERS?
- IN FACT,
WE CAN WRITE THEM NOW.
I BROUGHT WRITING MATERIALS.
- UM, YEAH.
- WE CAN'T USE THAT PAPER.
WE NEED PRETTY STATIONERY
AND I KNOW THE PERFECT PLACE
TO GET IT.
Kazumi: "DEAR SAKAI,
THANK YOU FOR TAKING THE TIME
TO READ THIS LETTER."
- Shana:
"YUJI, YOUR INSTRUCTIONS
ARE WRITTEN BELOW.
PLEASE READ THEM CAREFULLY."
- Kazumi: "SHANA AND I
HAVE DECIDED
THAT IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO MAKE A CHOICE."
- Shana:
"TOMORROW, DECEMBER THE 24th,
AT PRECISELY 1900 HOURS,
COME TO THE ILLUMINATION FIESTA
BEING HELD AT THE CLOCK TOWER."
- Kazumi:
"WHEN YOU'VE MADE YOUR CHOICE,
PLEASE MEET ONE OF US THERE.
WE WANT TO SHARE OUR FEELINGS
WITH YOU."
- Shana: "I'LL BE WAITING
AT THE NORTH EXIT."
- Kazumi: "I'LL BE WAITING
AT THE SOUTH EXIT.
KAZUMI YOSHIDA."
- "SHANA."
- ( letters sliding )
- WHAT THE--
- I'M KIND OF SURPRISED
THAT SATO DIDN'T LAUGH
OR MAKE FUN OF ME.
BUT--
- IF YOU LIKE YOSHIDA,
I THINK
YOU SHOULD JUST TELL HER.
WHO CARES WHAT SAKAI
OR ANYBODY ELSE THINKS?
- I DON'T HAVE THE GUTS
TO FOLLOW HIS ADVICE.
I WISH I COULD JUST TELL HER
AND GET IT OVER WITH.
BUT I KNOW HOW
SHE REALLY FEELS
ABOUT SAKAI.
AND I CAN'T HELP
BUT TAKE THAT INTO ACCOUNT.
SOMETHING'S GOT TO GIVE.
I NEED TO BE LIKE THE OTHERS.
- HEY, IKE,
DOING SOME SHOPPING?
- Ike: I--
I NEED TO CHANGE TOO.
COULD I HAVE A MOMENT
OF YOUR TIME TOMORROW?
- SURE.
I'M FREE IN THE AFTERNOON,
BUT I HAVE SOMETHING IMPORTANT
TO DO THAT NIGHT.
I'M KIND OF GETTING NERVOUS.
SHANA AND I DECIDED TO WAIT
FOR SAKAI IN DIFFERENT PLACES
AND HAVE HIM
CHOOSE BETWEEN US.
- OKAY, TOMORROW AFTERNOON
SHOULD BE PERFECT THEN.
I THINK YOU SHOULD KNOW
HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
- Kazumi: I HAD NO IDEA.
ALL THIS TIME
I THOUGHT IKE WAS TRYING
TO PUSH ME TOWARDS SAKAI.
WHY'D HE HAVE TO TELL ME
THIS THE NIGHT
BEFORE MY HEART
IS PUT TO THE TEST?
IF I'M NOT CHOSEN TOMORROW,
WILL I STILL BE ABLE
TO USE THIS
FOR SAKAI AND SHANA'S SAKE?
- SO TODAY I'M--
I'M GONNA TELL YUJI
I LOVE HIM.
- THAT WOULD BE
A POOR DECISION.
WHAT IF HE DOESN'T FEEL
THE SAME WAY?
WHAT WILL YOU DO?
WILL YOU BE ABLE
TO FIGHT ALONGSIDE SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T SHARE
YOUR FEELINGS?
EVEN IF HE WERE TO CONFESS
HIS LOVE TO YOU,
HE INDEED STILL CARES
FOR MISS YOSHIDA
AND THINKS OF HER FONDLY.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU DON'T KNOW THEM
AS WELL AS I DO.
- THIS IDIOTIC ATTEMPT
AT A FAIRY-TALE ROMANCE
COULD RUIN YOUR FRIENDSHIP.
- IT IS NOT IDIOTIC.
- YOU HAVEN'T GIVEN ME
ANY REASON TO THINK OTHERWISE.
- NOTHING YOU SAY
IS GOING TO STOP ME!
- STOP ACTING
LIKE A PETULANT CHILD
AND CONSIDER
WHAT'S AT RISK HERE.
- QUIT STICKING YOUR NOSE
IN MY BUSINESS!
THIS HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU!
- YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN NOW,
MILADY,
AND THINK
ABOUT THIS RATIONALLY.
- I'LL CALM DOWN
SOON AS YOU STOP TELLING ME
WHAT TO DO WITH MY LIFE!
- I'M YOUR GUARDIAN--
- I DON'T CARE!
- Tiamat:
ENOUGH, BOTH OF YOU.
- I'LL BE IN MY ROOM.
- Tiamat:
YOU FELT THE SAME ONCE.
- INDEED, TIAMAT.
WHICH IS WHY
I WANT TO PROTECT HER.
I KNOW THE AGONY
OF UNREQUITED LOVE.
I THOUGHT THE FLAME OF HEAVEN
WOULD SPEAK UP IN MY FAVOR.
BUT HE DID NOT
BECAUSE I WAS AT FAULT.
- ( knock at door )
- WHAT?
- Wilhelmina: WHAT TIME
WILL YOU BE LEAVING?
- WELL, I NEED TO BE THERE
BY 7:00.
- HAVE YOU DECIDED
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO WEAR?
- UH, NO.
- IF YOU'RE GOING
TO CONFESS YOUR LOVE TO HIM,
YOU MUST INDEED
LOOK YOUR BEST, MILADY.
- YEAH.
- IF YOU CAN TELL ME
WHAT COLOR AND STYLE
YOU WOULD PREFER TO WEAR
THIS EVENING.
I'M HAPPY
TO GO PICK SOMETHING UP FOR YOU.
- WILHELMINA.
- I KNOW
MY WORDS WERE HURTFUL,
BUT I HOPE YOU CAN UNDERSTAND.
I ONLY SAID THOSE THINGS
BECAUSE I AM CONCERNED
ABOUT YOUR WELL BEING.
INDEED, MY PLACE IS NOT
TO MAKE DECISIONS FOR YOU.
THEREFORE, I WILL NOT
MAKE ANY ATTEMPT TO STOP YOU.
- THANKS.
- SO WHAT
WOULD YOU LIKE TO WEAR?
- UH,
MAYBE SOMETHING PINK?
- ( tolling )
- I ASKED YOU HERE
TO TELL YOU THAT I LOVE YOU.
DON'T SAY A WORD.
JUST WALK
ONE WAY OR THE OTHER,
TO ME OR TO HIM.
- Yuji: THIS IS IT.
WHAT THE--
AHHHH!
- YUJI!
- Kazumi: A SEAL.
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji:
HECATE APPEARS OUT OF NOWHERE
AND STEALS THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD FROM ME.
BAL MASQUE'S SECRET WEAPON,
THE TAIMEI SHIHEN,
BEGINS TO AWAKEN.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND,"
"STIRRINGS OF PERIL."