- Alastor:
DESPITE MARGERY'S BEST EFFORTS
TO RESTORE THE DAMAGE
SHE CAUSED,
TANAKA IS TORTURED
BY THE MEMORY
OF OGATA'S LIFELESS BODY.
UNWILLING
TO FACE MARGERY AGAIN,
TANAKA BIDS FAREWELL
TO HIS FRIEND SATO.
ALTHOUGH THEY'D ONCE CHOSEN
TO FOLLOW THE SAME PATH,
THE BOYS
GO THEIR SEPARATE WAYS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( static over radio )
- Zarovee: WHAT WAS THAT?
THIS CONNECTION'S BAD.
I CAN'T HEAR A THING
YOU'RE SAYING.
YES, I UNDERSTAND YOU FEEL
THAT THIS RECONNAISSANCE MISSION
IS SOMEHOW BELOW YOU.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO SUCK IT UP
AND QUIT DRAGGING YOUR FEET
LIKE THIS.
OTHERWISE OUR PLAN
WILL INEVITABLY FAIL.
- ( static )
- COME ON, YOU DON'T WANT
TO BREAK LADY BEL PEOL'S TRUST
IN US, NOW DO YOU?
LIKE IT OR NOT,
WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER
TO MAKE THIS HAPPEN,
BIFRONS.
- ( static )
- UGH, JEEZ,
SIGNAL SUCKS OUT HERE.
- Bifrons: IT IS NOT THE SIGNAL
GIVING YOU TROUBLE.
I HUNG UP UPON MY ARRIVAL.
COLLATION FLUX ZAROVEE.
- AWFULLY RUDE OF YOU.
HOWLING FANG BIFRONS.
- RUDE?  I AM HERE
AT THE PRESCRIBED TIME,
AS ALWAYS.
A LOWLY JAEGER
SUCH AS YOURSELF
CANNOT FATHOM THE GREATNESS
OF MY PRESENCE.
MY TREASURE TOOL, TARNKAPPE,
GRANTS ME STEALTH,
BUT ONLY WITH CONSTANT EXPENSE
OF ENERGY.
- YES, I REALIZE IT TAKES YOU
LONGER TO--
- RARELY DO I FIND REASON
TO RUSH.
- I'M NOT RUSHING ANYTHING.
I JUST DON'T WANT
TO WASTE TIME.
WE MUST DESTROY THE MYSTES
AND RETRIEVE THE TREASURE TOOL
TO BE ATTACHED
TO THE TAIMEI SHIHEN.
BEYOND THAT, WE MUST DISPOSE
OF ANYONE
WHO ATTEMPTS
TO GET IN OUR WAY.
NOT A MISSION
TO BE TAKEN LIGHTLY.
- ( chuckling )
YOU NEED NOT WORRY.
I AM CAPABLE
OF SHOWING RESTRAINT.
I WON'T MASSACRE EVERYONE.
- WHY WOULD I WORRY?
( thinking )
AND THEY WONDER WHY I HATE
WORKING WITH WANDERERS.
- SHALL WE?
- YES, LET'S GET STARTED.
- NOW I WANT YOU TO TRY
WHAT I JUST TAUGHT YOU.
FIRST, YOU'LL NEED TO FOCUS
ON YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
HERE COMES THE HARD PART.
YOU NEED TO DELVE
DEEP WITHIN YOUR SUBCONSCIOUS
AND TAKE CONTROL OF ITS FLOW.
- BE CAREFUL.
- Yuji: YOU THINK
I COULD BE A SPELL CASTER?
- Wilhelmina: INDEED.
- WOULD I BE ABLE
TO CAST UNRESTRICTED SPELLS
LIKE MARGERY?
- WELL, YOU CERTAINLY
HAVE ENOUGH POWER OF EXISTENCE.
IT'S JUST A MATTER
OF TRAINING.
IT COULDN'T HURT
TO LEARN ANOTHER WAY
TO PROTECT YOURSELF,
ESPECIALLY IN YOUR SITUATION.
YOU'LL LEARN TO ATTACK
WITH YOUR FLAME.
- I COULD BARELY CAST A SEAL.
YOU SURE I CAN DO THIS?
- Alastor: POSITIVE.
YOU SIMPLY NEED THE TUTELAGE
OF A SKILLED SPELL CASTER.
BECAUSE YOU'LL BE DRAWING
UPON YOUR OWN POWER
OF EXISTENCE,
YOU WILL NEED TO LEARN
TO GAUGE THAT POWER,
OR YOU WILL SUFFER
DIRE CONSEQUENCES.
- YOU THINK THE CHANTER
OF ELEGIES WOULD TEACH HIM?
- I SUPPOSE THERE'S NO HARM
IN ASKING HER.
- WOULD YOU MIND TALKING TO HER,
WILHELMINA?
IF I CAN LEARN SPELL CASTING,
IT COULD SAVE MY LIFE.
- YES, BUT--
- PLEASE ASK HER.
WHAT IF YOU REMIND HER
I'M GOING TO BE
USING THE SILVER'S FLAME?
THIS IS HER CHANCE
TO WITNESS ITS POWER FIRSTHAND.
- Margery: OKAY.
THE NEXT THING YOU NEED
TO DO
IS COLLECT A SMALL AMOUNT
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE
IN THE PALM OF YOUR HAND.
WHOA, KID!
CAREFUL.
YOU DON'T WANT TO USE TOO MUCH
OR YOU'LL ZAP YOURSELF.
YOU ONLY NEED A SMALL FRACTION
OF WHAT YOU JUST COLLECTED.
GOOD.
NOW IMAGINE A FLAME
COMING FROM THAT POWER.
- Marcosias:
I GOT MY EYE ON YOU, PARTNER.
YOU'RE HERE TO TEACH THE KID.
DON'T DO ANYTHING SKETCHY.
- YOU REALLY THINK I'D RUIN
AN OPPORTUNITY LIKE THIS?
I'M ONE STEP CLOSER
TO FINDING THE SILVER.
- YUJI, I WANT YOU
TO THROW YOUR FLAME
AND HIT THAT TARGET!
- WHAT?
BUT HOW DO I--
- DON'T THINK ABOUT IT,
JUST DO IT!
HURRY.
- UH, RIGHT.
THROW THE FLAME
AND HIT THE TARGET.
- I GOT IT!
- YUJI!
- THERE'S NO NEED TO OVERREACT.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE BURN,
MILADY.
- ( grunts )
- WANT TO KNOW
WHY YOU GOT ZAPPED?
IT'S BECAUSE YOU STILL
HAD POWER IN YOUR HAND.
YOU'VE GOTTA USE ALL OF IT
IN YOUR ATTACK.
- RIGHT.
- KEEP PRACTICING
TILL YOU CAN HIT
ALL THE TARGETS
IN UNDER FIVE SECONDS.
- I'VE NOTICED THAT YUJI
SEEMS TO BE TAKING HIS TRAINING
MORE SERIOUSLY LATELY.
- A WELCOME CHANGE INDEED.
- Tiamat: HE'S IMPROVING.
- ( Marcosias laughs )
I GOTTA SAY,
THE KID DESERVES
A PAT ON THE BACK
FOR BEING ABLE TO KEEP UP
WITH MARGERY HERE.
- Alastor:
IT APPEARS HE'S COME TO GRIPS
WITH HIS SITUATION
AND IS DETERMINED
TO PERSEVERE.
- Margery: I'M NOT SO SURE.
- ( grunts )
- MAYBE IT'S JUST ME,
BUT I'D SAY HE'S TRAINING
AS IF HE'S POSSESSED.
- I DID IT.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
I HIT 'EM ALL.
- HMM.  NOT TOO SHABBY
FOR YOUR FIRST DAY.
- WHAT'S NEXT?
LET'S KEEP GOING.
I NEED TO LEARN HOW TO TAKE DOWN
A BIGGER TARGET.
CAN YOU TEACH ME?
- YUJI.
- JUST IN CASE
I COME FACE TO FACE
WITH ANOTHER DENIZEN.
- DON'T GET AHEAD OF YOURSELF,
BOY.
- ( laughing )
I'D LISTEN TO THE LADY
IF I WERE YOU.
DIDN'T ANYONE EVER TELL YOU
THAT PATIENCE IS A VIRTUE?
- RUSHING THROUGH YOUR TRAINING
WOULD BE MOST COUNTERPRODUCTIVE.
- Tiamat:
SO TAKE YOUR TIME.
- OKAY.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT,
YOU WANTED
TO CARRY BLUTSAUGER.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS CREATE A MARKER FOR IT
IN YOUR MIND.
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO CALL IT FORTH
WHENEVER YOU NEED IT.
- THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
- WHATEVER.
NOW YUJI,
ONE THING TO KEEP IN MIND--
YOU WON'T FIND YOUR RESOLVE
IN YOUR HEAD.
YOU HAVE TO FEEL IT
IN YOUR HEART.
- REALLY?
'CAUSE I DON'T SEE
WHAT DIFFERENCE IT MAKES,
LONG AS I'VE FOUND IT.
- HMM.  I'M CANCELING
TOMORROW'S TRAINING.
YOU NEED SOME TIME
TO COOL OFF.
- HEY, YUJI, DO YOU WANT
TO COME OVER FOR A BIT?
- BUT YOUR HOUSE IS BACK
IN THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION.
IT'LL BE MORE THAN "A BIT."
- NEVER MIND.
I'LL JUST GO
AND BUY SOME MELON BREAD.
YUJI, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- UM...
- YOU SEEMED DIFFERENT
AT TRAINING.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE.
- NO, I'M FINE.
I KNOW THIS
MIGHT SOUND WEIRD,
BUT I'M FINALLY REALIZING
WHAT'S GOING ON IN MY LIFE.
I KNOW I'M BOTH A TORCH
AND A MYSTES.
BUT THIS MESS
WITH THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
AND WHATEVER'S INSIDE OF IT
GOT ME THINKING.
I CAN'T CONTINUE
TO LIVE A NORMAL LIFE
IN THIS CITY AS YUJI SAKAI.
I DON'T BELONG HERE.
I'M A PART OF THE WORLD
OF THE FLAME HAZE NOW.
AND I'M READY TO MOVE ON
FROM THIS PLACE WITH YOU.
BUT TO DO THAT,
I NEED TO BECOME STRONGER.
YOU TOLD ME THAT YOURSELF.
- YEAH.
- WELL, GOOD NIGHT.
- YEAH, GOOD NIGHT.
- ( echoing )
I'M READY TO MOVE ON
FROM THIS PLACE WITH YOU.
- MOVE ON WITH ME?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I SHOULD BE HAPPY RIGHT NOW,
BUT I'M NOT.
- I'M HOME.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YUJI, YOU'RE HOME.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I MUST'VE DOZED OFF.
- THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
YOU THINK YOU MIGHT BE
COMING DOWN WITH SOMETHING?
- I'M FINE.  OH!
I MADE SOME
ROASTED SWEET POTATOES FOR--
- MOM!
- I'M OKAY.
- THAT'S ODD.
SAKAI'S NEVER LATE.
OH, GOOD MORNING, SHANA.
YOU DIDN'T WALK TO SCHOOL
WITH SAKAI TODAY?
- NO,
WE DECIDED TO SKIP TRAINING.
- ANY IDEA WHY HE'S NOT HERE?
- HEY.
JEEZ.
I WISH HE COULD LET IT GO.
- MORNIN'!
SO I NEED TO DO
A LITTLE SHOPPING TOMORROW.
DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'D WANT TO COME?
- UH...
- UNLESS YOU HAVE PLANS.
- I'M FREE.
- THEN SAY YOU'LL GO.
PRETTY PLEASE?
I'D LIKE TO GET YOUR OPINION
ON STUFF.
THAT COOL?
- YEAH.
- AND SAKAI'S OUT TODAY.
APPARENTLY, HIS MOTHER
IS FEELING UNDER THE WEATHER.
HE SAID
IT WASN'T ANYTHING SERIOUS,
BUT SINCE HIS FATHER
IS AWAY ON BUSINESS.
HE THOUGHT IT WOULD BE BEST
TO STAY HOME AND LOOK AFTER HER.
- CHIGUSA'S SICK?
- GOSH,
I HOPE SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
- CHIGUSA.
- I FEEL BAD FOR SAKAI'S MOM.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- ARE YOU GONNA GO VISIT HER?
- I MIGHT.
I WAS THINKING
ABOUT COOKING THEM DINNER
AND TAKING IT OVER THERE.
BUT I DON'T WANT ANYONE
TO THINK THAT I'M USING IT
AS A CHANCE TO GET CLOSER
TO SAKAI.
- WHAT?  NOBODY WOULD
EVER THINK THAT OF YOU.
- I DON'T WANT TO BE A BOTHER.
- IF YOU ASK ME,
YOU'RE PUTTING
WAY TOO MUCH THOUGHT INTO THIS.
IF YOU WANT TO HELP SAKAI
AND HIS MOM, JUST DO IT ALREADY.
YOU SHOULDN'T CARE
WHAT ANYBODY ELSE THINKS.
- YOU THINK I SHOULD?
- YEAH, IF THAT'S
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.  THANKS.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
YOU ALWAYS KNOW
JUST WHAT TO SAY.
BETTER GET STARTED
BEFORE IT GETS TOO LATE.
SEE YA!
- AW, MAN, I KEEP
THROWING HER INTO HIS ARMS.
- IKE'S RIGHT.
IF I WANT TO HELP SAKAI,
THEN I SHOULD.
THERE'S NOTHING STOPPING ME.
I GUESS THE SAME GOES
FOR USING THIS.
I THOUGHT
JUST HAVING A TREASURE TOOL
WOULD MAKE ME A PART
OF SAKAI'S WORLD.
BUT THAT'S NOT TRUE.
IT DOESN'T CHANGE A THING.
BUT ONCE I USE IT,
I WILL BE
A PART OF HIS WORLD,
EVEN IF ONLY
FOR A BRIEF MOMENT.
I WAS WORRIED
I'D NEVER HAVE THE COURAGE
TO GO THROUGH WITH IT.
BUT IF I WANT TO SAVE SAKAI,
I HAVE TO.
NOTHING'S STOPPING ME.
- Yuji: I'VE GOT RICE AND SALT.
WHAT ELSE IS SUPPOSED
TO GO INTO PORRIDGE?
- YUJI!
HEY, WHERE'S YOUR MOM?
- SHE'S IN HER ROOM SLEEPING.
- ( grunting )
( knocking )
- SHANA, HEY THERE.
COME ON IN.
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
YOU'RE NOT IN ANY PAIN,
ARE YOU?
- I THINK IT'S JUST EXHAUSTION.
I'LL BE UP AND ABOUT AGAIN
BY TOMORROW.
I'M SORRY,
I DIDN'T MEAN TO WORRY YOU.
- IF YOU NEED ANYTHING,
JUST LET ME KNOW
AND I'LL GET IT FOR YOU.
YOU REST.
- THAT'S SWEET OF YOU.
THANKS.  JUST HAVING YOU HERE
MAKES ME FEEL BETTER.
- I'LL COME BACK TOMORROW
WITH WILHELMINA!
- THAT'S OKAY.
THERE'S NO REASON TO BOTHER HER
WITH MY SILLY FATIGUE.
SHE IS A BUSY LADY.
- SHE WON'T MIND.
SHE'S THE GREATEST NURSE EVER.
ONE TIME I HAD A BAD FEVER,
SO SHE BROUGHT A GIANT BLOCK
OF ICE HOME
TO TRY AND COOL ME OFF.
- YEAH?
( laughs ) YOUR POSITIVE ENERGY
IS INFECTIOUS.
- IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN GET FOR YOU?
- UM, SORRY WE HAD YOU WORRIED.
- I'M JUST GLAD
IT WAS NOTHING SERIOUS.
- SHE MAY NOT LOOK IT,
BUT MOM'S PRETTY STRONG.
HER ILLNESS
DID GET ME THINKING THOUGH.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- WHAT'LL HAPPEN TO HER
WHEN I LEAVE TOWN.
MY DAD'S AWAY SO MUCH.
AND WE DON'T HAVE
ANY RELATIVES.
SHE'D BE ALONE A LOT.
WHAT IF SHE WERE
TO COLLAPSE AGAIN?
KNOWING HER,
SHE'D JUST GET RIGHT BACK UP.
HEY, I FORGOT,
ONE OF HER FRIENDS IS A NURSE.
SHE'LL BE IN GOOD HANDS.
- SO YOU'RE NOT WORRIED
ABOUT LEAVING HER ALONE?
- NO.
WHAT GOOD WOULD IT DO TO WORRY
WHEN I KNOW
THERE'S NO WAY I COULD HELP?
- OH, DEAR, THE LADY'S ILL?
- YEAH.
- THEN I MUST DO SOMETHING.
SHE'S DONE SO MUCH
FOR THE BOTH OF US.
THE LEAST I CAN DO
IS CREATE A REMEDY FOR HER.
- Shana:
YUJI SAID HE'S NOT WORRIED
ABOUT LEAVING HER,
BUT I DON'T THINK
HE'S BEING HONEST.
- I KIND OF THREW IT TOGETHER
AT THE LAST MINUTE,
SO I'M SORRY
IF IT'S NOT VERY GOOD.
BUT I MADE DINNER FOR YOU
AND SOME SOUP FOR YOUR MOM.
- WOW, YOSHIDA.
UM, THANK YOU.
- I HOPE SHE'S FEELING BETTER.
I'LL BRING MORE TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
- Yuji: I CAN'T LET THIS GO ON
ANY LONGER.
I HAVE TO TALK TO HER,
AND SOON.
- 'MORNING.
HOW'RE YOU FEELING?
- OH, MUCH BETTER.
I WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR LOOKING AFTER ME YESTERDAY.
- NO PROBLEM.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
SPEND TODAY IN BED TOO.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS THE WEEKEND,
AFTER ALL.
- I KEEP GETTING
THIS WEIRD FEELING.
- HERE, WHY DON'T YOU GO
AND TAKE THIS MEDICINE
TO CHIGUSA?
I'LL MEET YOU THERE
ONCE MY PACKAGE FROM OUTLAW
HAS BEEN DELIVERED.
ALL RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
- I CAN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
YOU SEEM A LITTLE DOWN, MILADY.
- NAH, I'M FINE.
REALLY.
SEE YOU THERE.
KAZUMI?
- Yuji: I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T ACCEPT IT.
YOU AND I
COME FROM TWO DIFFERENT WORLDS.
YOU SAW YOURSELF--
I'M NOT EVEN A HUMAN BEING
ANYMORE.
- I KNOW.
BUT THAT DOESN'T CHANGE
THE WAY I FEEL.
- THE LONGER I STAY HERE,
THE MORE TROUBLE
I'LL ATTRACT.
THAT'S WHY I'VE DECIDED
TO LEAVE TOWN WITH SHANA.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF WHEN.
I'M AS GOOD AS GONE.
SO I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR
TO KEEP TAKING GIFTS FROM YOU.
- SAKAI.
- I'M SORRY.
- WHY ARE YOU APOLOGIZING?
IF THE WAY I FEEL
BOTHERS YOU FOR SOME REASON,
THEN JUST SAY THE WORD.
TELL ME TO BACK OFF
AND THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO.
AT LEAST I WOULD KNOW
HOW YOU REALLY FEEL ABOUT ME.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE TRYING
TO AVOID THE SUBJECT.
I'M NOT TRYING
TO BE A NUISANCE, SAKAI.
I LOVE YOU
EVEN IF
YOU DON'T LOVE ME BACK.
- YOSHIDA.
WAIT!
SHANA.
- YOU KNOW WHAT THE PROBLEM IS?
YOU.
I KNOW WHY KAZUMI GOT MAD
BECAUSE I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
YOU'RE LYING TO YOURSELF.
DEEP DOWN YOU'RE
WORRIED ABOUT YOUR MOM
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO LEAVE.
BUT YOU WON'T FACE THE TRUTH.
FORGET IT.
I'M NOT GOING
ANYWHERE WITH YOU.
WHAT AN IDIOT.
- THEY WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
I'M FINALLY ABLE
TO DEAL WITH MY SITUATION.
I'M NOT LYING TO MYSELF.
I'M NOT.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG, MILADY?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING
TO TAKE THE REMEDY TO CHIGUSA?
- WHAT DO I DO?
I'VE NEVER SPOKEN TO SAKAI
LIKE THAT, BUT--
- HAVING A ROUGH DAY,
ARE WE?
THAT'S TOO BAD.
I'M AFRAID...
IT'S ABOUT TO GET WORSE.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
MY NAME IS ZAROVEE.
I AM KNOWN
AS THE COLLATION FLUX.
- A DENIZEN?
- THAT'S RIGHT.  PLEASED
TO MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
- WHY DIDN'T I SENSE
HIS PRESENCE?
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji: I'M AMBUSHED
BY THE CRIMSON DENIZEN ZAROVEE,
WHO HAS A STRANGE REQUEST.
EITHER I FOLLOW HIM
THROUGH THE CITY
OR HE'LL CONSUME ITS CITIZENS.
AS WE WALK,
I TRY TO COME UP WITH A WAY
TO ALERT THE OTHERS.
WHAT DOES ZAROVEE
WANT FROM ME?
AND WHAT TROUBLE
IS ON THE HORIZON
FOR SHANA TOO?
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND,"
"WHAT COULDN'T BE SAID."