Some fish can never be caught
because they belong to the sky.
Who we are?
Where do we come from?
And where are we going?
No one thinks about these questions.
We go to work.
Day in and day out,
we laugh, we complain,
we buy things,
we eat, and we sleep.
Somehow a century has already gone by.
I am 117 years old now.
As I often tell people,
the legend says that mankind came from the ocean,
and that when our life's journey as
human beings on this earth is done,
our souls return to the sea as beautiful fish.
No one believes me when I tell this story.
They call me an old fool.
But I know it's true.
I can see them in my dreams, giant
fish swimming down from the sky.
I can hear them calling out to me
and their lovely voices awaken my memories.
Long, long ago, when the Earth was young,
all that existed was a vast ocean and
the great primordial fish that lived in it.
These ancients were the first
incarnations of the human soul.
That's why, from the moment we're born,
the ocean calls to us
and eventually we return to it.
My name is Chun.
I come from a world beneath the ocean.
The sky of our world is connected
to the oceans of the human world.
Once freed by death,
human souls drift down from their world to ours
and it is our task to look after them and keep them safe.
We are the ones who control time,
the tides, and the changing of the seasons.
We are not human beings but neither are we gods.
We are The Others.
Look! Sister Leizu's woven a new sky for the humans.
Hurry, Chun. The Rite of Passage is about to begin.
We'll hurry, Chisongzi!
Sister Leizu!
I need to join the Rite of Passage.
Can we borrow two horses?
I don't mind if the horses don't.
I'll take this one.
Of course!
You like 'em big and strong, don't you?
That's why you like...
Wait for me!
Wait up, Chun!
No way!
Oh, yeah?
Qiu, tell me about the human world!
I loved it there.
I almost didn't want to come back.
Maybe you shouldn't have!
Then who would keep you out of trouble?
You're the one who's in trouble, slowpoke!
The Rite of Passage is starting! Hurry!
Let's go, come on!
I can't believe it's finally here.
Now you be careful in the human world.
I will.
Chun! Over here!
Coming, Mother!
Hey!
Yeah! Looking good, Grandma!
The seasons pass before us all,
Earth and Heaven, Moon and Sun, tied by the elements.
You'll be all on your own up there in the human world.
Here. You need to eat more.
Mother, I'm full.
Are you gonna come back?
I'll be back. Don't you worry, OK?
The sun above shines on the earth below,
and the friendly gods, their blessings bestow.
For seven days you will roam the human world
and observe the natural laws that we govern.
But remember this,
you must not have any contact with humankind.
Dragon of the sea and sky,
awake!
Let the gateway be opened!
You heard him. Keep away from the humans.
The farther away the better.
I know.
You hear?
Chun won't get into trouble.
She's a clever girl.
Tell that to Ah King.
Her girl never came back!
What are you waiting for?
I can't hold this up forever!
Remember, you must get back to the gateway in seven days.
You can't be late...
Mother...
Or you'll be left behind.
The soup. Out of the way.
My little girl has grown up.
I should go.
Chun...
Be careful.
I will.
Keep track of the time.
You run along now, Chun. Go on.
Don't worry. Goodbye.
Chun! Wait!
The human world is beautiful, but dangerous.
Remember, your world is here.
So long, Chun!
Try not to miss me too much!
Behave yourself up there!
Every child who has turned 16 in the past year
is sent to the human world in a Rite of Passage...
to see for ourselves how we control the rain, the wind,
the sun, and the stars.
We have been taught how dangerous their world is
but seeing it for ourselves,
it didn't seem dangerous at all.
It was magical and so beautiful.
I had never been happier.
Look!
The red dolphins came back again.
I knew that they would,
just like last year at the same time!
Come on. Let's say hello.
Hey!
Up here!
Good to see you again!
For six days, I explored the human world.
I saw great wooden sailing ships,
and lights that flickered and danced across the heavens.
I saw the candles that the humans lit
to accompany the souls of the departed on
their journey down the rivers to the sea.
I followed them,
and on the seventh and final day,
I too, returned to the ocean.
It was time to go home.
Watch this!
You like that?
Well, just you wait.
What are you doing?
Dolphin bait. Get my back, will you?
OK.
Come here, you.
Wait right there.
I will.
Look at all the fish!
What were you doing down there so long?
Chasing a red dolphin.
Do you see it?
There's something different about her.
I can feel it.
I'd lost track of the time.
The seventh and last day was nearly over.
I had to get back.
I was running out of time.
The gateway wouldn't stay open much longer.
Where?
Out there. By the whirlpool.
It's a dolphin.
Yeah.
The red one from before.
She's caught in the net.
I'm gonna try and cut her free.
Go fetch my knife.
What about the whirlpool?
I'll be fine. Don't worry.
Go get it.
Thanks.
Brother, be careful!
OK, all right.
Brother!
I'm trying to save you.
Come back! No!
Where is he? Where's my brother? I want my brother back.
I want him back and everything to be all right.
Please, Brother. Don't go away!
Come back!
Chun! You're back! Thank heavens!
What's the matter? Chun, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Come on. Let's talk at home.
Thank goodness you're safe.
I've made your favorite dinner.
Good morning, Grandmother.
Is Grandfather up?
Grandfather, where do humans go when they die?
Their body is turned back into
the dust from which they were made.
And their souls?
They go to Ascendance Palace where
they are transformed into tiny fishes.
And watched over by Ling Po, the Lady of Souls.
Will we die too, Grandfather?
Of course we will.
Death is part of the natural order of things.
In fact, your grandfather's time is almost over.
No! I don't want you to die.
Now, now, sweet child.
Death is not an end just as birth is not a beginning.
They're just stops on the path to eternity.
I knew grandfather was right, of course.
Because I knew I was destined to inherit his powers,
and how could I do that if he did not die?
But knowing of things true is
not the same as wanting it so.
What's that you're playing, child?
Who's there?
Your flute sounds like something from another world.
It's not mine.
The sound is very pleasing.
Where did it come from?
The human world, a boy...
He's dead now...
because of me.
So that's why you're here. A human boy.
Perhaps the Lady of Souls can help you.
Come back here at midnight tonight
and bring that bell with you.
Ring it and someone will come for you.
I will be here waiting.
Did I do that? Sorry.
Where you going? Kinda late, isn't it?
The bell.
That's it.
Now get ready.
I had made my choice. There was no turning back.
The moment I stepped aboard that boat,
I knew my destiny had changed forever.
You came alone?
Follow me.
Sit.
Thanks. I'd rather stand.
What brings you to the Island of Souls?
There's a soul I'm looking for.
The soul of a human boy.
What time was it he died?
It was two days before the Wheat Harvest.
You need to be sure of the date,
otherwise you're searching for a needle
in a haystack, so many die every day.
I'm sure.
It was my birthday.
I know what you're trying to do, girl,
and it goes against the laws of nature.
I don't care.
I've got to save him.
The punishment is harsh for those
who defy nature no matter who you are
so you should care!
But I owe him... for saving my life.
How very touching.
I've been stuck here for 800 years,
and I'm still not done paying penance for my sins.
But you didn't...
Don't interrupt!
Let me tell you what real tragedy is.
Meeting someone you care about so much
you forget yourself and make a mistake.
So then you go back and you try to
fix it and make things right again.
And then you learn that fixing it is impossible.
We could never undo the wrongs we've done, this I know.
You're saying you won't help me?
I'm saying I pity you.
Besides, resurrecting someone
from the dead doesn't come cheap.
What would it cost?
No less than a lovely girl's loveliest features.
Your eyes.
Now she's scared.
Don't want to give up your pretty eyes?
All right. I'll take half of your life instead.
If that'll save him,
take it.
No, no, no! How many times do I
have to tell you? Not on the carpet!
Why do you have so many cats?
Who else would spend half of
eternity with an old bore like me?
Humankind came from the ocean.
That's why people's tears and
blood are salty like the sea.
From the moment they are born,
their lives are journey homeward
though they are unaware of this.
They think they follow a path of their own choosing.
They meet, they part.
Some grow old, some do not.
But when they die,
the voice of the sea speaks to the soul
calling all of them back
and each swims off to their own separate destiny.
This is the Hall of Souls,
where all human souls are kept after death.
So many souls.
Will you be able to find him?
He won't look the same as he was.
I'll know him when I see him.
I didn't even know his name,
but I remembered everything about him...
the scar on his forehead,
the way he looked at me.
I searched in there for hours and hours,
all night long.
And then...
Well, you see?
It requires a piece of your soul to wake him.
Now your lives are bound together.
It's up to you to protect him and guide
him through all the difficulties ahead...
until he's grown enough to return to his world
and be restored to life.
Now there's no turning back. Do not fail him...
or his soul will vanish into the void...
Forever.
Lazy rascal.
Where were you all night?
And where did you get that?
No.
I'm Chun. Remember me?
I'm the red dolphin you saw.
I suppose you don't remember your name.
I'll just give you a new one.
My name means begonia.
One day I'll look after all the begonia trees like Mom.
Don't worry. You won't always be small.
You'll get bigger,
bigger than this fish bowl,
and the mirror, and the table.
And the bed even!
Bigger than this whole room!
And this building!
What's with all the racket? Keep it down!
Anyway, I'll give you a good name.
You cannot keep a fish here.
Who asked you? Go away.
Wait! I can keep a secret.
You can trust me.
Hey! I know a good name for him.
What?
Open the window.
There's a fish in the Northern Ocean.
His name's Kun and he's enormous.
I mean so big that he can't even be measured.
That's what the ancient books say.
So anyway, this Kun is gigantic,
and get this. He can fly. Yeah!
He's got wings that are the size of clouds!
Are you finished?
Goodbye.
From now on,
Your name...
is Kun.
Kun?
Rain this time of year. That's unusual.
It's salty.
You're growing.
You wanna play, don't you?
Remember when a red dolphin played in the sea with you?
Remember that?
You do remember!
Come here. I wanna try something.
You can fly!
It's true.
Just like your namesake.
Amazing!
Your family's calling you. They want you to come home.
Kun, you keep growing, OK?
I'll get you home again.
Promise.
Kun?
Mother, were you in my room?
Yes. What's wrong with that?
What did you do with him?
I threw it out.
Time you stopped playing with that thing.
Mother, that thing is a human life!
What? Come back here! What did you say?
Chun.
Stop following me.
Where you going?
You all right?
My mother threw Kun away.
Don't worry. I know where to find him.
Here! Over here.
Nasty. But I bet he's there.
Kun?
It's him.
Grab my feet. I'm gonna look.
What? You can't go in.
You sit tight. I've got it covered.
Besides, your mother would have a fit if you got lost too.
Qiu! Be careful!
I knew it'd be nasty but not this nasty.
Qiu,
thanks for doing this.
Kun? Kun?
Rats! Lots of 'em!
Won't these rats try and eat Kun?
You can be sure of it.
They'll strip him to the bone, they will.
What an enchanting scent.
That provocative perfume.
Smells like... love.
How can I help you, handsome?
What brings you to my neck of the woods?
I'm looking for a fish.
A fish?
Well, as it happens, I've seen a fish.
Really? You know where Kun is then?
That's no ordinary fish, is it?
You got it from the Lady of Souls, didn't you?
Ling Po gets all the good people
who turn into fish when they die.
I get all the bad ones who turn into rats.
I think my rats are much cuter
than her slimy fish, don't you?
So you'll help me find him?
No, sorry.
Unless...
You let me borrow your sweetheart for a dance!
Relax. Go with it. Music!
Ready, baby cakes?
Just follow my lead.
Chun!
There are two things that boys need to learn...
how to dance,
and how to control their own little rats.
It's a wonderful place, isn't it, the human world?
You've been to the human world?
Look. They caught one.
Kun!
In you go.
That's it.
Is he all right?
He's not waking up.
He's alive!
Such a pure soul.
Yes, he's sure to grow into a big fish indeed.
I found ya!
There you are.
Now where'd they go?
There you...
Grandpa Houtu! Grandpa Houtu!
There's a fish. I saw a fish. A big fish.
Here. Down in this well.
But it was there before.
I saw a fish. I swear!
The unseasonal weather, the salty rain,
these are bad omens.
We must stay vigilant, every one of us.
Good thing I saw them coming.
If they'd found him...
This is your new home, Kun.
OK?
Hey, I think there's something hiding in there.
Come on out!
Chun! Watch out!
Qiu!
Stay back!
Watch out! It has two heads!
Now you tell me?
Get off of me!
Take this, snake! And that! And that!
And that!
Qui! That's enough!
You OK?
Qiu!
Chun...
I feel so tired.
I just wanna go to sleep.
No, don't fall asleep. You've got to stay awake.
How about a song? I'll sing you a song.
The moon and stars hanging above the sea
The moon shines...
You're not very good, are you?
If it was pretty, it would put you to sleep.
Where are we?
We're almost there.
Don't you dare go to sleep.
Grandfather!
Help!
He has been bitten by a two‐headed serpent.
There is no known antidote to its venom.
Grandfather, save him! Please!
Chun...
This is for you.
There is perhaps one way.
Chun, wait outside. I will do what I can.
Thank you.
Hey! You're getting me all wet. You've got fish breath.
Qiu! Thank goodness you're OK!
Alive and kicking thanks to your grandpa.
He's pretty good.
Pretty good? He's the master of all herbs and plants.
He's awesome!
Dearest old friend,
can you still remember the day when we first met?
Soon I was to find out what it
had cost my grandfather to save Qiu.
Grandfather.
Chun...
come here.
It's time for me to go.
It's 'cause of what I've done, isn't it?
No. No, child. Don't blame yourself.
It is the natural order of things.
Life and death are one thread.
I must tell you something, Chun.
The course you have chosen is not an easy one.
Everyone will be against you.
But if your conscience is clear,
then it doesn't matter what others think.
Simply follow your heart.
I will become a begonia tree
and reunite with your grandmother,
but I will always be here to support you.
Grandmother had been the master of birds.
When she died, she turned into a
phoenix and kept Grandfather company.
Two days after we talked, Grandfather was gone.
All the birds came to visit that day.
It felt like Grandmother had come back as well.
Snow in midsummer.
The seasons have fallen into chaos.
Something is coming.
Isn't this crazy weather? It's great!
I love the snow!
Do you believe God exists?
No.
I do.
No one's ever seen him.
Humans have never seen us, but we exist.
I won't be here when my parents get as old as Grandfather.
Just when they need me to look after them...
I'll be gone.
What are you talking about?
I traded half my life away.
You did what?
I traded it for Kun.
Chun!
There you are! Get down here at once!
I gotta go.
Chun!
Coming!
You can't really believe my daughter is responsible!
She's connected to it somehow.
The Elders are beginning to suspect Chun.
She and Kun are both in danger.
Who are you?
Don't you recognize me, handsome?
If they find Kun, your sweetie will be punished.
You must hide him in the river inside the mountain cave.
Go on. Go on, hurry!
Chun's in big trouble...
and it's all 'cause of you.
Come on.
As long as you're here she's in danger.
If you care about her you'll leave.
Now.
Where's Kun?
He's gone.
Gone? Gone where?
I set him free.
He's in the river.
Chun, wait!
I was trying to help you!
A token. Just what I needed.
You're my ticket to the human world.
Kun...
I thought I'd never see you again.
Let's follow them. They'll know the way out of here.
Chun...
I didn't have parents growing up like you did.
Just my grandmother.
She does her best and I love her,
but the only thing I've ever really cared about
is you.
Now I realize
how much you care about him.
I was scared.
I don't wanna see you hurt.
Please let her wake up.
Kun!
Kun, it was you who woke me, wasn't it?
I don't ever wanna lose you again.
She's OK! Yeah!
Isn't that great?
Chun's OK!
Your turn.
What a terrible hand!
Well, since you're here, you might as well come in.
I'm sorry to bother you...
Triple.
I have a question.
What?
Why did you give that human soul to Chun?
It was a trade, not a gift!
If you're willing to pay the price...
There's not a thing in this world that can't be traded.
Even half a lifetime?
Well, aren't you the clever fellow?
So, I can give half my lifetime and trade for hers.
Of course. However, the price just went up.
You'd have to trade your whole life.
Fine.
I should warn you, however...
Even that's not gonna save her!
That little girl's life is tied
to that great big fish of hers.
When it dies, she dies.
What if the fish returned home?
If the fish goes back...
On the very day it leaves...
She'll die too.
There must be a way to save her.
Mahjong! I win!
Come play a round. You might even win.
The table's full.
There.
Now it isn't.
Wow. That's lucky. I win.
I don't believe...
What's luck anyway?
Good luck, bad luck. It's just fate, really.
It's all up to you now.
What?
I said it's all up to you now.
All in your hands.
Goodbye. Thank you.
You young kids live life like a worthless
rock you found by the side of the road,
while old hags like me have to rack our
brains figuring out how to live another day.
Without joy, what's the point of a long life?
What would we give up?
What sacrifices would we make for those we love?
What are we willing to risk losing?
Half our lives, our family and friends,
and the world we know?
By the time we ask ourselves these things,
if we ask them,
it's usually too late to matter.
We already know the answer.
What have you got to help me forget something?
You sure you want to?
Real forgetting is not that difficult.
But it hurts.
Feeling pain can be a good thing.
Do you have anything that'll make it go away?
There is something.
It will make you forget all your sorrows,
but all your pleasures as well.
Mengpo potion.
Well, maybe just some wine.
Got something for a hangover? It's my first drink.
Do you even know who's in love with you?
And the things he's done for you?
He's forsaking everything,
betraying everyone...
for your happiness!
The sea is flowing backwards.
The heavens are angry with us.
Only by destroying that creature will we set things right.
I can tell you where the big fish is,
but first, you will have to break the
seal and allow me to see the sunlight.
Things are getting awfully messy.
I think it's time to clean it up.
Well, baby? Are you ready?
The great fish comes and we must go
To get to higher ground
We shall all go up to the mountain top
While the waters gather round
The rains come down, the rains come down
Till the land becomes the sea
Old home gone, get your new home on
Where will my new home be
Pei, terrible news.
Someone has taken the Dragon mask!
Chun! Listen to me.
Get away from it right now.
Leave that monster to us.
Don't hurt him. He's not a monster.
Ungrateful child!
Mother, forgive me.
Feng, why do you stop?
Go. Destroy it!
No, I'll do it.
You had your chance.
Kun. Go. Fly!
Don't let it get away!
Fly, Kun. Fly!
Go, Chun! Now's your chance!
Get Kun back home! Go on!
Heavens, no.
Hurry, Chun!
Get him out of here while you can!
Qiu!
Qiu, stop!
You're not strong enough to control the gateway.
Just watch!
We need Pei. Go find his grandmother. Hurry!
I can't hold on much longer!
Chun! Get going!
Go, Kun!
I'm finally going back to the human world!
Thanks for the help, handsome!
I'll think of you from up there.
What have we done?
Sorry, sweetie, but without a token from the
human world, you can't pass through the gateway.
Grandfather saved us.
Kun, be strong.
Our fate's have been connected since the day we met...
and I don't regret it.
Brother Songzi, what will we do if we don't find everyone?
We'll find them.
OK.
Grandma.
Down there! There's people in the water!
Help! Help!
Over here!
It's Tingmu and his sister!
Take her first!
Little sister!
Has anyone seen Qiu?
No, not yet.
Tingmu is still out there. We have to go back.
I'll come with you.
Tingmu!
Kun, don't give up now.
You have to fly and get through the gateway.
Go on. I'll be all right. Don't worry.
Grandfather will protect me.
Now go while you can!
Go on!
Down there. It's that creature.
Quick. We mustn't let it get away.
But first, let's find Tingmu.
If that monster escapes, our
whole world will be destroyed.
We can't wait.
Go, Kun!
Go!
Kun!
Fly! Fly, Kun!
Grandfather.
Please help.
What should I do? Tell me.
What can I do?
Please save him.
Please, Grandfather.
Grandmother! Here!
He's done nothing wrong.
Why are you protecting him?
He died saving me, now I need to save him!
His little sister is waiting.
Tingmu has been swept away in the flood.
What about his sister?
Run. Everyone, run!
Get to higher ground. Go. To the mountaintop. Hurry!
Over here. Help me make a bridge.
The others need us. We have to go help them.
I've got to help my family.
I can't go with you.
My brother!
Chi Songzi!
Where's Tingmu?
Did you find Tingmu?
I'm afraid not.
What?
I'm sorry.
Mother!
Mother, I'm here to help!
No! We don't need any help from you!
Please, child. Go.
Give me my Tingmu back.
I want Tingmu to come back.
Hurry, everyone. We must hurry.
Stay calm.
Hold the water back!
Hey.
Feng!
It's all my fault.
Everything bad that's happened
is because of what I've done.
The one good will be if you make
it back and live your life again...
as it was before we met.
Fly, Kun.
Go home and live your life...
a beautiful life.
I'm coming, Grandfather.
Ma!
Tingmu?
It's me!
Up here!
Tingmu!
Mama! It's me!
Look, it's me!
Oh, Chun!
Chun!
Finally, the moment's here.
Why haven't you left?
Here. Sister Leizu wove this for you.
Try it on. It should fit.
Thank you.
Why am I here?
Am I dead?
No, child.
But you've lost all your powers.
You can't stay here.
What about the others?
Don't worry. Your sacrifice saved them...
and now the balance is restored.
Go south till you come to the Southern Sky
Pools. You can accompany him on his journey home.
But know that when he returns to the human world,
he won't remember you or any of this.
All right.
You'll tell my mother I'm still alive, won't you?
Go now.
Thank you.
No need for that.
A deal is a deal.
You should thank the one who
traded away his life for yours.
Chun! Chun! Hey!
Over here!
Wait up! I'm coming with you!
I can't swim!
What you thinking?
There's so many...
So many stars.
Whenever I look up at the sky,
it's like I hear someone calling to me.
What do you think?
There's something I've been wondering.
Does love last forever?
Like the stars?
Yeah.
Once Kun is safe,
we'll go home, right?
My powers are gone.
I can't go home.
The human world is nice.
Is that where you want to live?
With Kun?
Impossible. I don't belong to his world.
I wasn't asking if it's possible.
I asked if it's what you want.
Here.
You know, you look cute when you're eating.
I know you pretty well by now.
I've seen all of you.
When you're tired, when you're angry,
when you're sad,
even embarrassed.
It's all beautiful.
You're like a brother to me.
Right.
You awake?
Uh‐huh.
You cold?
No.
You should sleep.
Qiu?
Thank you for always being there.
You treat me better than anyone else ever did.
Will we ever see each other again?
Would you recognize me?
We will meet again.
And despite what Ling Po said,
I know we will recognize each another,
no matter how much we'd changed.
Kun!
Leave now.
It's time to go home.
Qiu!
Quick! Take hold of my hand!
Come on, hurry! We don't have much time!
What's happening to you?
I fixed it so you can live...
in Kun's world.
But aren't we going home together?
I got your life back for you
so you can go with him if you want.
No.
Wait!
No!
Stop it!
Chun, listen...
Listen to me.
Listen.
It's OK.
Qiu.
You know this is right, Chun.
You have to go.
Trust me on this and I know we'll meet again.
I wish I'd...
I wish I'd held you closer when I could have.
Just one time...
Come on.
When I count to three, we jump, OK?
Trust me!
One,
two,
three!
When you see the wind and rain,
think of me and I'll be with you...
Always.
Qui...
Goodbye, Chun.
No!
Do you believe in miracles?
We each spend countless cycles waiting...
waiting for the chance to
enjoy this adventure called life.
It's so easy to forget how precious life is, how short.
It's lost in a thousand little moments of not caring.
It doesn't hurt to be braver,
to be more grateful, more loving.
There are many things I don't understand,
and many questions I can never answer.
But one thing I do believe,
that the heavens gave us life
so that each of us can create miracles.
It's time, my friend.
From now on,
you'll be taking over for me.