Homura...
I am sorry.
But I wanna be a magical girl.
Madoka...
Don't do it!
I finally figured it out what I wanna wish for.
I know what I want now more than anything else.
And I'm ready to trade my life for it, with no regrets.
But you can't!
If you do then,
everything I've fought for...
...it's all for nothing!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You've been protecting me for a long time,
and I'll never forget that.
I know you're the reason
that I'm the person I am today.
I'm so sorry.
I really want this.
It's the answer I've been looking for,
I swear.
I promise I won't ever let your efforts be in vain.
Believe me, Homura.
Madoka...
You are the center of karmic destiny
from many different timelines,
so no matter how enormous your wish,
it most definitely will come true.
You're sure it will?
Of course!
Madoka Kaname,
what is the wish which you would trade your soul for?
I wish...
I wish I had the power to erase
witches before they're born.
Every single witch,
from the past, present and future,
everywhere.
Ah...
That wish...
Once it's granted,
it would unravel the fabric of time itself!
It violates the laws of karmic destiny!
Uh? Are you trying to become a god?
I don't care what I become.
All the magical girls,
who believed in hope and fought witches,
I don't want them to suffer or cry anymore.
I want them to be at peace.
And if that goes against the laws of universe,
then I'll just rewrite those laws.
That's the only thing I want.
It's what I wish for.
Now, grant my wish,
Incubator!
Madoka, do you know how scary that wish you made was?
Sort of.
You'll be fighting an endless battle,
one that stretches from the past to the future,
and for all eternity.
You'll never be the same.
You won't exit as a physical entity anymore.
Dying would be a kinder fate.
For the rest of time,
you'll live on as an entity,
whose sole purpose is to destroy witches.
I know.
And I'm ready.
If someone ever tells me it's a mistake to have hope,
well then, I'll just tell them they're wrong,
and I'll keep telling them 'til they believe.
No matter how many times it takes.
Sounds good to me.
Huh?
If you think you can do it, do it!
I mean, you've found your reason to fight, yeah?
And you ain't running away anymore, right?
So, there's nothing holding you back!
Anyway, now it's time to get your
ass in gear and go full steam ahead!
Thanks a lot, Kyoko.
If that's what you really want,
then it's time you got this back.
Here you go.
Hehehe...
You are not just giving us back our hope,
but you are becoming hope itself,
the hope of magical girls everywhere.
That's enough.
It's all right now.
You don't have to hate anyone anymore.
And you don't have to curse anyone anymore either.
I'll go back before you turned into this,
and take the burden of all your pain.
Uh...
Ah!
Where is this place?
The universe is in the process of reordering itself,
based on Madoka's new laws of reality.
That's right.
Your magic gives you the power
to travel back and forth in time.
Would you like to see how the existence
called Madoka Kaname meets her ultimate end?
That's the Soul Gem her wish created.
Impressive, isn't it?
No way...
The wish she made carries a heavy burden,
imagine all the curses she'll have to take on now.
With all the hope she's harnessing,
she's giving birth to a new universe.
But that means her eventual despair will be so great,
it would destroy another universe.
It's only natural.
Ahh...
No, it's all right.
Ah...
Remember?
I wished for the power to erase all witches.
And if what I wished for really did come true,
then even I...
...don't have a thing to worry about,
ever!
Madoka...
Because of your wish,
your life has no beginning or end anymore.
The proof of your life on earth is gone.
The memories people had of you don't exit.
You've crossed over onto a higher plane.
Your physical body is no more.
You're now a concept.
No one will ever sense your presence again,
and you will never be able to interact with anyone.
You are no longer a part of this universe.
What are you saying?
Do you honestly think Madoka would want this to happen?
After everything she's done,
this is her reward?!
I don't believe it!
I can't believe it...
This is worse...
than death...
Uh-uh.
That's not true, Homura.
Now I can see everything that's ever happened,
and everything that ever will.
I see all the universes that could have been,
and all the universes that are waiting to be born.
Really.
Madoka...
I see it all,
and I finally know...
I know all the things you've done for me
through out all those different timelines.
All of it.
All the times you cried and all the time you got hurt,
but you kept fighting for me.
I'm so sorry I never knew until now...
I'm so sorry.
Mm.
I had to become what I am now,
to really know the kind of person you are.
And you were there all alone,
the most amazing friend
someone like me could ever have.
I'm so glad I know now.
So, thank you, Homura.
For all that's happened,
you truly were my very best friend.
But...
what's gonna happen to you now that you're like this?
You don't have a home to go anymore...
You'll never be able to see your family and friends...
And you'll be stuck here,
alone by yourself forever and ever..!
Mm-hm.
But I'm not alone.
You're always going to be with me,
and so will everyone else.
Because from now on,
I'll be everywhere for all time.
Even if you can't see me or hear me,
I'll be right there by your side, Homura.
Madoka...
Is that what you want?
Even if I don't remember you ever again?
How am I gonna know you're there
when I can't even feel you're
standing next to me anymore?
Uh-uh.
It's a little soon to be giving up hope.
You managed to follow me all
the way out here, didn't you?
Besides, even though you're going back to your world,
maybe you'll still remember me.
I mean, you never know, right?
You'll see, everything will be fine.
Just believe.
Madoka...
We are magical girls, remember?
We make hopes and dreams come true.
They might not happen all the time,
but there's no doubt miracles can really happen.
Don't you think?
Madoka!
Please don't go!
Sorry.
I've gotta go meet the others now.
I don't know when, but I will see you again, Homura.
Promise.
So, until then, take care of yourself, okay?
Madoka!!!!
No.25, Kyosuke Kamijo.
I will be performing "Ave Maria."
Sorry.
I guess I caused you a log of trouble.
No.
I should apologize to you.
In order to save you,
I don't have a choice but to
erase everything that's happened.
But I if I do that, this future will have to disappear.
I know this isn't the way you
thought things would turn out,
but I do think this is the way you'd want it to be.
Your wish was a precious gift,
and you sacrificed so much for it.
I have to honor it, respect it.
Because it wasn't meaningless.
So...
Mm-hm.
I'm okay with that.
Yeah, I'm okay with that.
I mean, all I really wanted was
to hear him play again, you know.
I wanted everyone to hear him play that violin of his.
The more people the better.
Just remembering that again is enough for me.
I don't have any regrets anymore.
I guess one thing still bothers me a little.
That is Hitomi, so let it slide.
Kyosuke doesn't deserve a girl as cool as her.
I'm sure the two of them will be very happy, won't they?
Mm-hm.
Well, are you ready to go?
Yeah...
...Sayaka?
Ah!
Where's Sayaka?
What's up? She was just here!
She's gone.
The Law of Cycle said it has to be this way.
Sayaka used up all her power just now.
That last attack drained all of her magic.
That idiot!
What the hell? She didn't have to go out like that,
especially over some guy she was crushing on..!
Dammit!
We were just getting around to being friends...
It's the fate of all magical girls though.
I'm sure you understood that fact
when you first got your powers.
We're supposed to bring hope.
But once it turns into despair,
we have no choice but to disappear...
forever.
Madoka...
Huh?
What, Homura?
Who is this, Madoka?
Yeah, who is she?
Oh...
Madoka, Madoka!
Uh-huh.
You draw really well.
Looks just like her.
No, Tatsuya! That's not nice.
Don't go around pulling girl's hair, okay?
Madoka, Madoka, Madoka!
Oh, I'm fine.
I was walking by and noticed his drawing.
Madoka, is that right?
...Uh-huh.
Here I come!
Come on, then!
Yeah!
That's it!
Tatsuya came up with an imaginary
friend to play with when he's alone?
I guess it is not that strange for someone his age.
No, it's not.
I used to do that, too.
Wait.
Do you know who "Madoka" is?
Is she some kind of anime character or something?
I don't know, maybe.
I've heard that name before,
but I'm not sure where.
I must've met her somewhere...
maybe when I was out with Tatsuya..?
Hm...
It's funny...
I don't know why but when I heard that name,
I started getting all nostalgic.
Madoka...
It's cute name...
You know that the ribbon has
got to be the cutest thing ever.
And exactly the kind I like too,
same color, same style, everything.
You can have it if you want.
Hahaha...
Thanks, but I'm a little too old to make it work.
But if I had a daughter,
I would've made her wear one just like it.
Hmm...
Interesting.
I suppose the system you just
described could work, theoretically.
It was real.
Nothing theoretical about it.
Well, either way, how would we prove such a thing?
This reality with its rules,
it's the only one we have to go by.
So if the laws of the universe were all altered,
the method to verify it wouldn't exit.
And since you're the only one who remembers that world,
there's no way to prove your memories are real,
or it's something your imagination cooked up.
I'll admit, we don't know why Soul Gems
shatter when they can't be purified anymore.
That's the phenomenon we're still trying to figure out.
But going back to this witch concept of yours,
I find it very interesting.
As a method of collecting the energy
of human emotions, it's very appealing.
If that kind of system really existed,
us Incubators would've come up with a
completely different set of tactics.
Naturally, after all,
that's the kind of creatures you are.
There were a lot of intriguing
things about that witch world though,
we didn't have to fight wraiths as we do here.
Collecting curses in that other world
seems like it was a much simpler process.
It wasn't really as simple as you think.
And our relationship with you was
...a little on the rocky side.
Hmm...
I guess I'll never fully understand human values.
The air's thick with dread tonight, isn't it?
And these wraiths just keep coming
no matter how many we destroy.
There's no end to them.
Your complaining isn't going to help.
Come on, let's go.
Ah!
Sorry about that.
Are you okay?
Don't worry.
I won't let your wishes end in despair.
None of you have to hate anyone,
or curse anyone.
I'm here to take all that burden for you.
So please,
keep believing in yourselves,
to the very end.
Even though witches aren't born into this world anymore,
that doesn't mean the curses of the
world have complete disappeared.
They just changed their form, is all.
Now, they attack us from the shadows...
This world isn't worth saving,
tragedies and sadness will never truly disappear.
But even so, it's the place she once tried to protect.
I remember that.
And I will never ever forget it.
That's why...
I keep fighting.
Do your best...