Oh, hi there!
Mm.
It's for you.
Wow, thanks a lot for getting me this.
You're like these amazing experts to finding rare CDs.
Nah.
I guess I'm just lucky, is all.
This soloist's interpretations are pretty awesome.
Here, wanna check them out?
O-oh, sure if you don't mind.
I wish I could hook it up to a speaker and play it
loud, nurses would kill me though.
-- OP --
Tiro Finale!
Wow, Mami, you're so unbelievably cool!
This isn't supposed to be fun.
What we're doing is very dangerous.
Don't forget that, okay?
Roger that!
How come a Grief Seed didn't pop out this time?
It wasn't a witch.
It's a familiar acting without its master.
They don't carry Grief Seeds.
Oh, so that wasn't a witch.
It seems ashamed to have to fight and not get anything.
We can't really let familiars do as they want.
If we did, they'd eventually become the
same as the witch they split off from.
Well, shall we go now?
Have either of you decided what to wish for yet?
Uh-uh.
How about you?
Hmm...
That doesn't surprise me.
It's hard to think when you're under pressure.
Maybe it would help if you told us what you wished for.
I didn't mean to be nosey.
It's fine if you don't wanna say.
For me, it was different.
I didn't have the luxury of thinking about it first.
It's not that I regret my decision.
I'm alive after all.
And I think the life I have
now is better than being dead.
But if you have the chance to think
really hard about what you want,
you should take as much time as you need.
That wasn't an option for me.
Um...hey, Mami.
I was wondering...if you make a wish,
does it have to be for yourself?
Huh?
Let's say that, and this is just an example, okay?
Say there was someone who was
having a way worse time than I was,
would it be bad if I used my wish to help him out?
Are you talking about Kyosuke?
It's an example!
I'm not talking about anyone!
You can wish for whatever you want.
There's no rule that says you have
to be the one to benefit from it.
It wouldn't be the first time that's happened.
Actually that might not be the best idea.
If you use your wish to grant someone else's, you
should be careful you know exactly why you are doing it.
Are you really doing it for someone else's benefit?
Or the opposite, you're doing it for
that person's ever lasting gratitude.
Mami.
The motive behind the wish is
what matters most, you know?
That's kind of harsh.
I was just asking.
I am sorry.
But I had to say it now before it was too late.
If you're not 100% sure why you're doing
it, you'll most definitely regret it later.
I guess you're right.
Maybe I was being a little naïve there.
Sorry.
That's okay.
It's a hard decision to make, isn't it?
It's not something you need to rush into.
As far as I'm concerned,
the sooner you decide, the better.
Oh, please, haven't you heard?
Girls don't like pushy boys.
Deciding what to wish for is harder than I thought.
Even though I really want you to, I can't rush you.
Suggesting a wish is also against the rules.
Would wishing to be a magical girl be a bad thing?
Madoka, are you just looking to become powerful?
Oh, no.
I don't really care about that.
Although...
maybe I do a little.
I mean I'm not very smart.
I don't have any talents.
But if I could become a person who's
as wonderful and as cool as Mami is,
then that something, I know for
sure, will make me happy.
If you became a magical girl,
there's no doubt you'd be much more powerful than Mami.
Huh?
It's true!
Although a lot depends on the kind of wish you make.
Let me put it this way.
I can't even begin to guess how big
the Soul Gem you'd create would be.
I've never met a girl with the
enormous potential you have.
Oh, come on. You can't be serious.
You're joking, right?
No.
Madoka? Are you awake?
Uh-huh. What's up, Dad?
Oh, god...
Oh no, not again.
Come on, Mom.
W-water...
...stupid balding old coot...!
If he wants a damn drink so badly,
he can damn well pour it himself, damn it!
Thanks a lot.
You wanna have some hot chocolate with me?
Uh-huh. Sounds good!
Have you ever wondered why Mom loves to work so much.
I mean, it wasn't really her dream
to work for that company or anything.
What was it?
Hmm...
It's not so much about her loving to work.
She just likes doing her best.
Huh?
Sure the hours are long and she's
under a lot of stress most of the time,
but she loves the challenge she gets by overcoming it.
To her, nothing beats its feeling of satisfaction.
Hmm...
You see, working at that company might
not necessarily have been her dream,
but the way your mom's living her life
is actually kinda perfect for her.
A person can achieve their
dreams that way too, you know.
You mean the way she lives her life was her dream?
I bet there's people out there who'd
say it's not that big of a deal.
But you know what?
That's the thing I really love about your mom.
I respect the way she lives her life.
I think she's amazing.
Mm.
Don't you even care?
You do know you're leading innocent
people into danger, don't you?
What are you talking about?
Kyubey chose them.
They're a part of this now.
You're steering them into becoming magical girls.
And I guess you don't like that.
No.
Especially, since Madoka Kaname's involved.
Uh-huh.
I see.
You've noticed it too, have you?
Her incredible potential?
I won't allow it.
She won't become like us.
Afraid of someone stronger
coming along to challenge you?
That kind of thinking's only for losers.
I don't wanna fight.
But you leave me no choice.
Then just make sure you and
I never see each other again.
We are through talking after tonight.
Next time, you can bet we'll have it out.
Hey. Sorry for the wait.
What's wrong? Is he okay?
Wouldn't they let you see him?
I guess he didn't want visitors today or something.
And I came all this way.
Talk about rude!
Hey, what are you looking at?
Over there.
Can't you see it?
It's a Grief Seed!
It's about to hatch!
Oh, no!
Why is it here?
This is bad.
We have to get out of here!
A Labyrinth is about to open up!
You mean one of those mazes?
Madoka, do you have Mami's number on you?
Uh-uh.
What do we do?
I got it.
Go find Mami and bring her back here.
I'm gonna stay and keep an eye on it.
You can't!
It's too dangerous!
Besides, we still have time before the witch hatches.
But once the labyrinth pulls you in,
you won't be able to get out again.
Mami might not get back in time to save you.
But if the labyrinth opens up,
how will we know where the Grief Seed is?
We'll lose track of it.
I can't let that happen.
Not here anyway.
Madoka, you go on ahead.
I'll stay here with Sayaka.
Huh?
If we're not here,
Mami can use telepathy to track my position.
If the labyrinth opens,
Sayaka and I can follow the Grief Seed inside.
When Mami gets here,
I can guide her down the shortest route to it.
Thanks a lot, Kyubey.
Okay, I'll go get Mami here as fast as I can!
Are you scared, Sayaka?
Oh, yeah... of course...
All you have to do is make a wish.
If you do, I can turn you into a
magical girl right here and now.
I know.
If things get bad, I just might.
I'm okay for now.
But that's an important decision for me to make.
And if I can help it,
I wanna make sure I'm doing the right thing.
There it is.
Thank goodness, we made it.
I'm a little angry though.
Sayaka's taking a huge risk.
But in this case, it was a good call on her part.
This way, we don't have to
worry about the witch getting...
Huh?
Ah!
I thought I told you, I didn't wanna see you again.
Like it or not, I'm hunting this prey.
You should leave immediately.
Look, we're not going anywhere.
Kyubey and Sayaka are inside waiting for us.
Then I'll make sure they both get out safely.
Do you honestly think I trust you?
You...
idiot!
We don't have time for this!
I don't wanna hurt you, but you give me no choice.
Don't struggle, they'll only get tighter.
Listen to me,
I swear this witch is not like the others!
Be a good girl and I'll release you,
after I finish up here.
Okay then, shall we go?
Yeah.
No, don't!
Ugh...
Mami...
I, uh...
Yes?
I've been thinking really hard about
all the different wishes I can make.
Do you have a favorite?
Yes.
But...
um...
You're probably gonna think it's
naïve and get upset with me.
Let's find out.
What's the wish?
Well, there's nothing special about me.
I've never been good at school,
and I don't have any talents.
I'm scared this is the way my life is gonna stay.
All is asking for help and not being
able to help when people need it.
I can't stand thinking about it.
Uh...
But then I met you, Mami.
And you showed me what it's like to
stand up for people and really help them.
And then...
When I found out that I might
be able to do the same thing,
I don't think I've ever been happier in my life.
And that's my wish.
'cause if I can become a magical girl,
that would be a dream-come-true for me.
I might not be good at anything,
but if I can help people out like you
then I can be proud of the way I live.
That's the best thing I could wish for.
It won't be easy.
You will get hurt.
You won't have time to go on dates
or have fun with your friends.
I know.
But after seeing how you keep doing your
best, I really look up to you, Mami.
I don't deserve it.
You need a better role model.
Uh..?
I just pretend to be cool.
When I'm scared or hurt, there's no one I can talk to.
All I can do is cry on my own.
It's not fun...
being a magical girl.
I hear you, Mami.
But you're not alone anymore!
You're right.
I'm not alone.
I found someone who's willing to stay
and fight by my side from now on!
Will you really stay with me?
Yes.
If someone like me will do.
Oh, look at this.
It isn't the sort of behavior you'd
expect from a role model, is it?
I'm not very good at this sort of thing, am I?
Mami...
Anyway, make sure you know what you want.
A chance like this doesn't come around too often.
Yeah, I know.
It's a once-in-a-life thing!
It is a contract after all, so you might as
well try to get something out of the deal.
You could wish to be a billionaire,
or you could wish for the perfect boyfriend.
Yeah, I know but...
Okay, how about this?
If you can't decide on something to wish
for by the time I finish off this witch,
we'll have a feast!
And you can ask Kyubey for a fabulous cake!
Huh?
Seriously?!
Yes.
You could ask for the biggest
and most extravagant cake ever.
Ah...
Then we can throw a party for everyone.
A celebration to announce the two
of us becoming a magical girl duo!
But I...
I can't do something like that for a cake!
Then decide on something you want.
A cake...
Okay! I'm on it!
Today's a special day, so I'll make short work of it.
Wah. But...
Sorry I'm late!
Phew, thank god you made it.
Be careful.
It's coming!
Sorry for the interruption,
but this won't take long!
Gotcha!
Yeah!
Tiro Finale!
Oh, no...
Hurry!
Make a contract with me before it's too late!
Madoka!
Sayaka!
Wish for something!
Anything!
Hurry!
That won't be necessary.
This one is mine.
I'll kill it.
Ah!
A second later and you most certainly would be dead.
Never forget what happened here.
This is what it means to be a magical girl.
Give it back.
Hm?
Give it back!
It's hers.
It's Mami's...
It belongs to her!
You can't have it!
It belongs to Mami!
You're right.
But this can only belong to a magical girl.
Therefore, neither of you has any right to touch it.
Mami...
really was the nicest person.
But in order for us to understand what it takes,
the kind of courage it takes to fight,
she can't...
Miracles and magic are real.
Hm?
What's happening, Kyubey?
We're okay.
The witch hasn't hatched just yet.
Are you okay, Sayaka?
Heck yeah!
I'm so bored I'm about to fall asleep.
I wouldn't advise using large amounts of magic.
You might disturb the egg.
You don't have to hurry.
Just come as quietly as you can.
Got it.
Mami!
The Grief Seed started moving!
It's about to hatch!
Hurry!
I feel so light.
This is the first time I've
felt this happy during battle!
I'm not afraid of anything anymore.
Because, I'm not alone anymore.