[FUTARO] I can't believe
they each bombed four subjects.
Great.
I know we didn't have much time,
but all of them studied so hard!
Futaro! There's no talking about
school at the dinner table!
What kind of dumb rule is that?
Besides, you were the one
who hooked me up with this job!
You weren't always the whiz-kid
you are today, remember?
They'll get there.
Try not to worry so much.
Huh?
Wow, you mean there was a time
when Futaro wasn't a huge nerd?
Oh, yeah. In fact, your big bro
was a regular troublemaker,
same as his old man.
Really?
And don't think I don't know
about that old photo
you keep tucked
in your student handbook.
-Show me!
-Hell no.
I'm not gonna let-- Uh!
-Gotcha!
-Hey! Dad!
Yay! I wanna see it too!
[ISANARI]
Now. Let's look.
Whoa!
That can't really be him,
can it? How?
Ha, ha, ha!
That was around the time
you met that little girl
and became the way
you are today.
♪
Ugh. What are you
going on about?
[RAIHA] So, spill! Was she
your first love or something?
[FUTARO]
No, now drop it!
♪
Hmm. What are these?
[MIKU]
Croquettes.
[YOTSUBA] Really?
'Cause they look like rocks.
[MIKU]
I know they taste good.
Go ahead, try them.
[YOTSUBA]
'Kay, twist my arm!
[FUTARO]
Sweet, there's ohagi.
Down the hatch.
[BOTH gulp]
[FUTARO] Oh, it's a croquette!
Not bad!
-Are you kidding, it's awful!
-Says you.
You're just picky because
you're so wealthy and spoiled.
[YOTSUBA]
Oh, yeah?
Well, you don't have
any taste at all!
Zero stars, Miku!
-[MIKU] Which is it?
-[FUTARO sighs]
Yeah, yeah,
I'm a classless loser, I know.
Now let's start reviewing
those exams.
Wait!
-[FUTARO] Hmm?
-[YOTSUBA] Hmm?
I'm gonna keep making them
until they taste perfect.
-[YOTSUBA/FUTARO] Uhh...
-[MIKU] So eat up!
[FUTARO groans]
[YOTSUBA]
How's your stomach, Uesugi?
Miku should be back
with the medicine any time now.
[MIKU panting]
-[stomach rumbles]
-[FUTARO groans]
And I thought I'd get
some actual work done today.
Guess not.
That girl fed me
within an inch of my life.
[YOTSUBA] Yeah. I feel like
I'm gonna pop.
This only happened because
you had to play food critic!
I actually thought
they tasted pretty decent.
All you had to do was lie!
Trust me, if I had
told her a lie,
then Miku would have seen
right through it.
[sighs]
Then say something vague like
they've got an intense flavor
and leave it at that.
Be vague! That's brilliant!
I've learned something!
Okay, but that's not exactly
the kind of lesson
I came here to teach you.
-[NINO] Well, well!
-Huh?
Are you napping
in someone else's house?
No, let me guess,
somebody drugged you.
With the way
I'm feeling today,
I think I might like
for somebody to give me drugs.
[NINO]
Hmm. Whatever, I don't care.
Anyway, let's go out
and have lunch, Itsuki.
[ITSUKI]
Um, okay.
Crap! Yotsuba!
Uh, yeah? What's going on?
[FUTARO]
I need these two to stay here
so they'll study.
You can't let them
leave the house.
[YOTSUBA]
What should I do?
I don't know, lie to them
if you have to!
I'll do my best.
Oh, yeah!
By the station, there's this--
[YOTSUBA]
Wait, you guys, don't go!
Look at poor Uesugi!
He's suddenly come down
with some kind
of terrible rare disease!
We have to make him better!
-[NINO] Huh?
-A disease?
[FUTARO]
Come on, really?
You're a horrible liar!
[ITSUKI] Maybe he should go
to the hospital.
No! Uh, he can't,
-it's impossible!
-[ITSUKI] Huh?
It's the kind of disease
where you die if you move!
[FUTARO]
That escalated quickly!
He'll die? That's too bad.
-Let's go, Itsuki.
-Yeah, coming.
[coughing violently]
Uh-oh. I only moved a little,
and now look.
That's bad!
You need to lie back down
before it gets any worse!
Eh, he can just take
some medicine and sleep it off.
Um. No need to go out,
you can have croquettes
for lunch!
[NINO] On what planet
are those croquettes?
You should... Uh. Oh!
You're good at cooking, right?
Make him some porridge!
[FUTARO]
I'm sick because I ate too much.
Why would I need food?
♪
I guess that isn't
too much to ask for.
[FUTARO]
Now she starts being nice?
You don't mind it
with eggs in it, do you?
[FUTARO]
Uh, that's fine. Thank you.
I figured you were sick when
I saw you lying on the floor,
but I had no idea
it was this serious.
Yotsuba? Is there anything
I can do to help him out?
Let's see. Um...
[gasps]
Yeah, you should
probably hold his hand!
Remember how Mom
would always do that for us
whenever we were sick in bed?
She said it was
a magical healing spell!
That's different!
This situation is
nothing like that, okay?
Yotsuba. Would you please
stop talking for five--
-[grunts]
-Whoa, are you all right?
[ITSUKI] Well, if it'll help
you get better.
[FUTARO]
What?
[ITSUKI gasping]
Nope, can't do it!
[FUTARO] Wow, you must hate me
more than I thought.
Okay. We got them
to stay in the house.
Now what do I do?
[YOTSUBA] Try to get along
better, you two.
♪
And I want you to study
with the group!
Let's all take Uesugi's lessons
together from here on out!
It'll be a whole lot more fun
for everybody if we do!
♪
[FUTARO] I approached this
the wrong way.
It seems to be more effective
for Yotsuba
to tell the truth
than to do something dishonest.
I guess I'll think about it.
Okay! The porridge is ready now.
[gasping]
[FUTARO]
Oh, is that whole rice?
Each individual grain
is sparkling.
They really do buy
the good stuff here, huh?
[screaming]
Oh, god, it's burning
my face off!
Are you okay? I'm sor--
Hey. I thought if you
moved around, you'd die.
♪
[gasps]
[chuckles nervously]
It's a miracle!
Looks like it's you
and me again, Yotsuba.
[YOTSUBA chuckles awkwardly]
Right back to where we started
before the exams.
-I don't know about that.
-Huh?
[YOTSUBA]
Come on, haven't you noticed?
Normally, Nino would have tried
to find a way to kick you out,
but she didn't this time.
[FUTARO]
That was a coincidence.
[YOTSUBA] It's not just her
and Itsuki, either.
Ichika and Miku
are changing too.
Even I've picked up on it.
I guess I'm the only one of us
who hasn't improved any.
I mean, my grades
are still pretty sucky, right?
[chuckles]
I'm gonna have to disagree.
You were actually
the first one to change.
I'm lucky that at least
one of you girls was honest
and forthcoming with me.
Then again, maybe I'm giving you
too much credit.
The only reason
I'm sick right now
is because of your aversion
to telling lies.
[YOTSUBA] Do you know
why I always help you
when you're trying to get
everyone to study with you?
Well, that's no secret.
It's because you want
to get good grades.
[YOTSUBA]
Not exactly.
♪
It's 'cause I like you.
-[heartbeat pounding]
-[gasps]
You... do?
Fooled you. Ha!
I was just yankin' your chain!
That's what you get
for thinkin' I can't lie!
[laughs wildly]
[FUTARO]
I will never trust again.
[NARRATOR]
And so, on that day,
Futaro's already hardened heart
grew a little colder.
[YOTSUBA singing]
Time to go camping!
Time to go camping--
Hey, Uesugi!
The school camping trip
is coming up!
Yotsuba.
[growls]
[screaming]
It's me.
Oh, you scared me.
Who the heck is that?
It's me again.
I'm sorry.
I guess I forgot.
-He's gonna kill me!
-It's still me.
Where's he keep coming from?
-Somebody please help me!
-[clears throat]
No shouting in the library.
-Sorry, ma'am.
[YOTSUBA]
So, what are you doing
with all these creepy
Halloween masks?
[MIKU] He's helping organize
the test of courage.
Wow. Wouldn't have expected that
from a loner like you, Uesugi.
Well, I'm not
doing it voluntarily.
My class is the one in charge
of the test of courage,
and when they picked
the committee,
I was studying instead of paying
attention to the teacher,
which meant the job
got relegated to me.
Talk about bad luck.
He brought it on himself.
Oh, let them have their fun.
I'll exact my revenge soon.
It'll be an evening
they'll never forget.
You're committed to this.
It wasn't very nice of them
to make him do
all the prep work by himself.
I'm giving Class One
a piece of my mind!
[FUTARO] Nah, don't bother.
Miku's right.
-I did bring this upon myself.
-But still.
[FUTARO] And besides,
it's not like I care
about camping, anyway.
Okay! Then let's try
to think of some things
that'll make you
more excited about it!
I was talking to some
other kids in my class,
and they said that
our school's camping trip has
a special legend
to go along with it!
On the last night,
there's always a dance
around the campfire.
It's really fun and romantic!
The rumors say that anybody
who's paired up
when the music stops
is destined to spend
the rest of their lives
together!
[giggles]
[FUTARO]
That's unrealistic.
-And stupid.
-[MIKU] Mm-hmm.
You guys! You're such a drag!
We're talking about dancing
in the firelight
and finding true love!
Isn't that the least bit
exciting to you two?
-Well, time to start study--
-[ICHIKA] Yoohoo!
[FUTARO]
Hey, you're late.
What's the clown face for?
[FUTARO]
Irrelevant.
-Today's math day.
-Sorry, I can't.
I have a shoot to go to now.
Speaking of which.
I thought of a way to let you
know in advance next time.
Huh?
Let's trade contact info.
[FUTARO]
Contact info?
I don't know
if that's necessary.
Yeah, I think
that's a fantastic idea!
Please, Uesugi!
I want you to be able
to reach me anytime, too!
Oh, but first,
there's something else
I need to take care of.
That oughta do it.
Hmm? Yotsuba.
What are you making?
Or should I even ask?
[YOTSUBA]
A thousand cranes!
They're a gift
for my friend's friend
who's away at the hospital.
That isn't studying!
Let me do half.
Once we finish this,
it's straight to work!
[YOTSUBA]
Okay.
-[MAN] Oh, Miss Nakano.
-Huh?
Hello, sir.
Glad I found you.
Would you mind
putting these papers
on everyone's desks
for me, please?
[YOTSUBA]
Sure thing.
[FUTARO]
Damn, how much of a pushover
can one girl be?
[gasps]
Wait.
I know what she's up to!
Is she buying time
so she doesn't have to study?
If that's her game,
then she's even more
of a devious mastermind
than Nino!
-'Kay, I'm off to work.
-[MIKU] Good luck.
Yeah, break a leg, sis!
[buzzing]
[ICHIKA] If you don't want
this photo to get around,
then you'll have to collect
everyone's information!
[gasps]
[giggles]
[FUTARO] As your tutor,
I need to be more involved.
I don't know, maybe I should
get your contact info!
[MIKU]
Sure, I can give you mine.
Woohoo. Two down.
I guess this means
I'll just have to try
and get Nino's
and Itsuki's another day, then.
[YOTSUBA] I'm pretty sure
I saw them in the cafeteria.
-Come on, let's go!
-Hey! Don't go!
I didn't get yours yet!
Uh, here. I gave you mine too.
-[MIKU] Thanks.
-[FUTARO] Yotsuba, wait up!
[giggles]
♪
[NINO]
Absolutely not.
Not even
if the world was ending.
Yeah, I can't think
of a single reason
why we would ever want
to contact you.
I had a feeling you would say
something rude like that.
But wait, that's not all!
Act now and you
will receive a bonus.
Raiha's info, absolutely free!
It's a once-in-a-lifetime offer!
[grunts]
[ITSUKI]
Fine, I guess I have no choice.
I can't believe
you'd sell out your own family.
A small price to pay.
You gonna give me yours, Nino?
[NINO]
Don't be ridiculous.
-[FUTARO] Suit yourself.
-[NINO] Hmm?
I guess that means
we'll have to chat without you.
Who knows what things you're
gonna miss out on, though.
Okay. Give me something
to write it down on.
[FUTARO chuckles]
Here you go.
Good job, Uesugi.
Now you've got everyone's.
You wanna check your math there?
Huh?
Ichika. Miku.
Itsuki. Nino.
Yotsuba! That's me! Bingo!
[FUTARO]
Her stupidity scares me.
Here, go ahead
and take mine too, then.
[buzzing]
[FUTARO]
Somebody's calling you.
Huh?
The basketball club captain?
What does she want?
I thought you were done.
Uh...
Um, almost.
I had one tiny thing left
to do for them, that's all.
Oh, gosh, would you look
at the time!
Sorry, Uesugi,
but I gotta go now!
[FUTARO] Again, that girl is
a terrible liar.
[FUTARO grunts]
Hey!
I wrote my info down for you.
Hey there, everybody,
how's it going?
Hi, Nakano. Thanks for helping
us out the other day.
Don't mention it.
[FUTARO]
I knew it.
She must have had
some important business here
to tell such an obvious lie.
[GIRL]
Anyway, I wanted to ask,
have you given any thought
to joining the club for real?
[gasps]
I have. Thank you so much
for inviting me.
[FUTARO]
So that's what this is about!
Turns out Yotsuba
really was trying to find a way
to weasel out
of our study sessions!
That's great news! So, uh...
[YOTSUBA]
Well...
I'm sorry, but...
I'm gonna have to say no.
I know you and the rest
of the team really need my help
and I'm letting all of you down,
but I have something important
in the afternoons now.
[ALL gasp]
Um, but if you want,
I could still fill in
whenever you have a game.
Well, that's that.
I can't force you to join us.
Although I think
it's a huge waste of talent
not to have you.
I don't have any talent at all,
but there's somebody
who pushes me anyway.
♪
[YOTSUBA sighs]
Huh!
Oh. Hey, Uesugi.
What brings you here?
I was on my way to the library.
Okay, but this club wing's
in the totally opposite
direction of the library.
That's kinda weird.
Are you done
with what you came here for?
I'm gonna keep working you hard,
so be ready.
Right!
I can handle it!
[FUTARO]
Thank you, Raiha.
[RAIHA]
No prob!
Oh, I forgot.
I should probably message
the quints and let them know
about the weekend session
I'm planning for them.
Wait. Just four?
[gasps]
My student handbook!
Did I never get it back
from her?
♪
[snoring softly]
[footsteps approaching]
♪
Give me
my student handbook, now.
♪
[NINO]
Get out!
♪
You're unbelievable.
What kind of creep barges
into a young lady's bedroom
without permission?
Well, I gave him permission.
Yeah, and what gives you
the right to do that?
Listen, I apologize.
I only did it because I need
my student handbook back
as soon as possible.
You're not usually so meek.
You must be hiding something
important in this thing.
[FUTARO]
If she sees that old photo,
there's no telling
what she'll do to me.
Good morning, Futaro.
Oh, and Nino.
You wanted this, right?
You sure you can do it?
What? I told you
of course I can!
I'm not a baby.
[scoffs]
Wha...
[NINO] Any other time,
I'd rather drop dead
than let you into my room.
Fine, I'll leave,
as soon as I get my handbook.
Here's the deal.
I'll give it back to you
if you pierce my ears for me.
Wha...
Do you want
your stupid book or not?
Let's get it over with.
Uh. Just do it yourself.
Yeah, no thanks!
Too scary.
Then why do you want it
done at all?
Look, it'll hurt for a while,
are you prepared for that?
Oh, what do you know?
It's not like
you've had it done before.
[FUTARO]
Uh, that's true.
[NINO]
I just want it, okay.
I guess it's because
everyone else I know has it.
[FUTARO]
Okay.
Fine then.
♪
I can't think of
a better opportunity
to get back at you
for the grief you've caused.
Here goes.
I need that book.
♪
[FUTARO] Five. Four.
Three. Two.
One. Zero!
Is what I'll say, okay?
[NINO]
Quit messing with me!
[screaming in pain]
-[FUTARO] Oh, crap!
-Huh?
Whoa, he looks like a bad boy.
He's exactly my type!
Who is this?
[FUTARO]
That'd be me!
Um, he's one of my relatives.
But that picture
was taken a while ago, so...
Wow.
Well, I can tell who got all
the good looks in your family!
Think you could
set me up with him?
Maybe. Eventually.
[NINO]
Oh, yeah!
My sisters and I used to be
adorable little angels
back in the day, too.
See? Hey, look at it.
Not interested, huh?
I think I'll go show it to
the girls for old times' sake.
That was close.
Oh. Done already?
Well, I gave it
some more thought,
and I decided
I shouldn't rush it.
As long as I have pierced ears
by the time I'm wearing
my wedding dress, I'll be happy.
Anyway, check out
this blast from the past!
[YOTSUBA] Oh, wow,
we look so young there!
[FUTARO] Well, she ended up
seeing my photo.
Good thing it was only half.
[YOTSUBA]
Aw, we were so adorable!
[ICHIKA]
When was this taken?
[MIKU]
In sixth grade.
[ICHIKA]
This was Kyoto,
so it must have been
from our school trip.
[FUTARO]
Five years, huh?
The color's fading a little.
[YOTSUBA]
This takes me back!
[ITSUKI]
We've really changed a lot
since those days, haven't we?
[FUTARO]
I hope we meet again.
[QUINTUPLETS]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[MIKU]
Yotsuba's the sporty one.
[NINO]
But does she know all the rules?
[YOTSUBA]
Huh? Sure I do!
[ICHIKA] What are the rules
for basketball?
[YOTSUBA]
Put the ball in the basket,
and you get two or three points!
[MIKU]
That's it?
Oh, and after practice,
you always eat a snack!
[NINO] I don't think
that's a requirement!