Okay, this sucks.
Yeah.
So, you're sure
we're locked in, right?
Yup.
That's it. I'll just have
to break the door down.
Stand back for a sec.
Wait, not yet.
Isn't that a burglar alarm?
If you damage the door,
the security guards might come.
[FUTARO] Great, that'll mean
we get out of here
that much faster!
Hold on, let's think
about this!
Something like that could get
the whole school sent home!
Besides, if Miku found out
we were in here.
♪
Fine then.
Maybe you can disarm it.
Hmm?
[giggles]
Yeah, sure I could,
if I was like ten feet tall.
Don't be absurd.
Come over here.
I'll help you up.
♪
[heartbeat thumping]
[ICHIKA] Stay calm.
Forget the burglar alarm.
My heart's beating
even louder than that!
♪
You better not say I'm heavy.
-You okay?
-[FUTARO] Yeah.
Here goes.
-[ICHIKA] Um, what's wrong?
-This feels familiar.
Have I been here before?
Hey, this is no time
for you to enjoy
how great my thighs are!
True, I'm about
to be squished by your weight!
[ICHIKA]
Excuse me?
What did I just say?
♪
If we don't want
to get in trouble,
we have to turn
that sensor off.
[BOTH straining]
FUTARO]
Never mind, let's just wait.
[screams in pain]
I have a question, teach.
What is it you're
doing over there?
I'm making a fire, of course.
Camp won't be fun
if we catch cold.
For a smart guy, he can be
pretty stupid sometimes.
Well, there's nothing to do,
so let's talk about
something fun.
Not right now.
I'm trying to focus on this.
I can't believe
Ichika's not back yet.
[ITSUKI]
Yeah.
She said she had a few things
to do for the campfire,
but that was a while ago.
[YOTSUBA]
Miku! Itsuki!
Have either of you
seen Uesugi anywhere?
It's the weirdest thing!
He was helping the campfire
group with our chores,
and now I can't
figure out where he is!
I checked the room
and the dining hall!
He's just gone!
He probably wandered off
to study or something!
[ICHIKA] Are you sure
you're okay with that?
Well, I'll try to look
after him then.
Just leave it
to your oldest sister.
Be right back.
I'm gonna go look!
Wait, Miku!
[ITSUKI]
What's that key for, Yotsuba?
[ICHIKA] Oh, you'll get
a kick out of this!
The other day,
Itsuki was like...
So, that wasn't good for Nino.
And as soon as she saw
that croquette, she was all...
Ugh, never mind.
Not one peep.
You're gonna make
Big Sis cry again.
He still hasn't asked me
why I cried, though.
Maybe he doesn't care.
I mean, why did I, anyway?
♪
I think I might quit school.
Wha...
I knew that would get
your attention.
Are you being serious
right now?
Technically, I would
just be taking a break.
Okay. Cool!
[MAN] And cut!
Nice work, Ichika.
[ICHIKA]
So, you know how I've been busy
filming this new movie, right?
I'm starting to get
more work now.
My career's really
been taking off.
Usually, actors my age
take a year off of school
when they have a big project.
Or they move to a school
that has
a more flexible schedule.
And come on, we both know that
there isn't much of a future
for me in academics.
I'm pretty sure
I won't miss school at all, heh.
Besides, Miku might be
better off that way.
[wood scraping]
[FUTARO]
That's good.
You found something
that you want to do.
Fine by me.
Wait! What happens to my pay
if you drop out of school?
I'm out twenty percent!
[ICHIKA sighs]
Your reaction surprised me.
[FUTARO]
You fail at life!
[ICHIKA]
I expected a full rampage.
Is that how you see me,
as some big tyrant?
♪
[ICHIKA]
Tell me, Futaro.
What's the real reason
you study?
Truth is, I kind of envy you
for having options.
Well, there's still a 99 percent
chance that you'll fail.
That sounds like you!
[FUTARO] I think it'll be
a good experience.
And if it works out,
that's great.
It's worth a shot.
Most things are.
-Futaro?
-Ichika?
[ITSUKI] I wonder
if the two of them are...
[MIKU]
It'll be okay.
[ITSUKI]
Miku.
It's fine if he's with Ichika.
[crackling]
♪
-I don't mind.
-Huh?
You know,
about the campfire dance.
You're right,
it's probably better
if we call the whole thing off.
Oh.
But hey, I've got an idea.
♪
We can dance now.
I mean, we even have
our own private campfire!
♪
[FUTARO]
Sure. Not like anyone's looking.
All right!
I knew it, you were embarrassed!
Obviously.
That's so adorable.
[heartbeat thumping]
I can do this without
my heartbeat giving me away.
I mean, it's awkward enough
without this whole legend thing.
People would make assumptions.
Wait, legend?
Oh, you didn't know?
I heard about it from Yotsuba.
It says if you dance
with someone at the campfire,
you'll be together for life.
[gasps]
[ICHIKA]
Oh.
Does Miku know that?
Yeah. She was there too.
Oh no, I wasn't trying
to interfere.
[FUTARO]
What's wrong?
She wanted this so badly.
And I took it away.
Look, Futaro!
[creaking]
Watch out!
[gasps]
[FUTARO grunts]
Whew. That was close.
Jeez, Ichika.
You're pretty clumsy, huh?
[heartbeat thumping rapidly]
[alarm blaring]
Hey, let go of me!
I'm trying to!
[BOTH scream]
[electronic voice]
Disturbance detected.
Please unlock
within thirty seconds.
If system is not disarmed,
security will be alerted.
Not good.
We gotta get outta here now!
[ICHIKA]
Yeah!
-[screams]
-What the hell is this crap?
Sprinklers, duh!
In case of fire!
Let's stop the sensor first.
But how do we do that?
Aren't we supposed
to use the key?
Key? It's never simple.
[alarm stops]
-Huh?
[ITSUKI] The key was sitting
right outside.
Ichika.
So, this is where you've been.
What were you guys doing?
♪
It's the last day of camp.
I had to explain the shed
incident to the teachers.
We both got in serious trouble.
Itsuki and Miku were skeptical.
I hope I get another chance
to tell them nothing happened.
How did an innocent school trip
end up like this?
Hurry up, Miku.
We're gonna get some food.
Okay. I'll be right there.
[door closes]
[MIKU] If the five of us
really are equal, then...
what am I supposed to do?
Man. I'm so sorry.
I can't believe
I had to get sick now.
Just my luck, right?
You were careless.
Even if it was just
an accident.
Now, stay in bed and think
about what you did wrong.
[ICHIKA]
Harsh!
Well, no reason to stay
in here and watch over me.
Just go skiing.
[ITSUKI]
But...
I'll come and find you guys
when I'm feeling better.
Oh, I know. You're having
trouble facing Futaro now.
[gasps]
[ICHIKA]
You've been tiptoeing around him
since that time at the inn.
Okay, so that was you I saw.
Just three months ago,
when I asked him to help me
with my schoolwork
that day in the cafeteria,
I had no idea.
Things have gotten
so complicated.
Are you sure Futaro's as bad
a guy as you make him out to be?
[ITSUKI] That's not what
I'm talking about!
[shudders]
Think I'll sleep more.
Hey there, Uesugi!
[FUTARO]
Yotsuba!
[YOTSUBA]
You're not getting out of this
just because it's optional.
[FUTARO]
Uh, what?
[YOTSUBA]
Come on, let's hit the slopes!
Yeah!
Whoo! I wanna go
on all of 'em!
And I wanna go back
inside and sleep.
Besides, I've never been
much of a skier.
[YOTSUBA] No way.
Sleep is for the weak!
It's okay if you can't ski.
I'll hold your hand
all the way down if you want!
Hey, who wants to study?
Wait, where are
your simpleton sisters?
Ichika's sick in bed today,
so Itsuki's taking care of her.
I guess that's to be expected,
after all that stuff
that happened.
Stuff?
By the way, you can't go around
locking doors without checking.
Huh? That's kinda random.
Well, Nino already
started skiing.
There you are!
[FUTARO]
Who's that?
Miku.
Wow, really?
Man, you're all so hard to tell
apart from just your faces.
♪
Uh...
[grunts]
[giggling]
Not too graceful, huh?
Are you okay? Here.
Uh...
Yeah. I'm all right.
This is great!
I'm always the one who has
to learn stuff from you guys.
But today, I'm doing
all the teaching!
[gasping]
Wow, you kinda suck.
What's up?
It's freezing cold out here!
Who am I talking to now?
[chuckles]
Aw. It's Ichika.
Oh.
Hey, Ichika!
I take it you're feeling better?
Yeah, I'm not
a hundred percent, though.
Okay, so where's Itsuki?
I thought she was
taking care of you.
Nah, she's out here.
She's skiing by herself because
she's not ready to face you.
Ichika! I keep trying
to teach these goofballs,
and they won't listen to me!
Get over it, that's every
single day of my life.
[giggling]
Why don't we make it
more interesting, then?
-Huh?
-[ICHIKA] Let's play tag.
Yotsuba's the best,
so she's "it."
-Sure!
-But what about the others?
Easy, if I find 'em,
then I'll tag 'em!
Okay. One! And two!
-Hey, count slower!
-[YOTSUBA] Three! Four!
-This sucks.
-[YOTSUBA] Five...
I literally just learned
how to go forward.
Wait a sec.
This is my chance
to explain myself to Miku!
Miku! Do you think
we could maybe--
Whoa, slow down!
We need to talk!
Damn. I didn't know I was
dealing with a speed demon here.
[panting]
I can't catch a break.
There's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
Ichika.
Did you tell anyone
about last night?
Huh?
I'm thinking
I might quit school.
No, I would never tell.
So that means...
Listen.
Um, how do you stop
this thing?
[ICHIKA]
What?
Aah!
Uesugi!
[screaming]
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
[chuckles]
Yotsuba.
When you teach someone,
you have to be thorough.
[WOMAN]
Are you okay over there?
[MAN]
Dude, are you dead?
[FUTARO]
Nope, perfectly fine!
Don't mind me!
Great, everyone's staring at me.
I don't know if it's because
I gave away
the charm Raiha made for me,
but my luck's been atrocious
since yesterday.
I know this bandage.
Is that you, Kintaro?
It is you, isn't it?
♪
[FUTARO]
Huh? Kintaro?
What kind of dumb name is that?
[NINO]
You jerk!
I think I'd recognize
who I gave this to.
Crap. Now what?
Hey, you can't just run away!
Maybe I should tell her now.
About how I lied at the test
of courage last night.
[NINO]
Come back here!
[FUTARO] What's the best way
to handle this situation?
They've got me cornered!
Ah, looks like
I've finally found you.
Gah!
[NINO]
Wait, Kintaro!
[YOTSUBA]
Uesugi, I'm coming for ya!
Ugh! I'm getting dizzy.
-There you are!
-Ha! Got you!
[BOTH]
Huh?
-Hey, Yotsuba.
-Guess you're "it" now.
Did you happen to see
a blonde guy come this way?
I don't think so.
Have you seen Uesugi?
That's so weird.
I wonder where he is.
Miku?
That was close.
You almost got caught there.
[FUTARO]
Is this an igloo?
Did you make it yourself?
[MIKU]
No. I just found it.
[FUTARO]
I see.
It's pretty cozy in here,
isn't it?
Um, Futaro?
It's cramped.
So, don't move too much.
You're right, I'm sorry.
Okay. I'll get out.
♪
I want you to stay, though.
Ugh. I don't know anymore.
Miku?
♪
[MIKU]
It's just,
well, what if Yotsuba's
still out there?
[FUTARO]
Good point.
I'd better stay
for a little while longer.
[MIKU]
Yeah.
[FUTARO] Where does she get
that endless stamina, anyway?
Of all of you, I'd say
she's the odd one out.
I'm lucky. Without the igloo,
she'd catch me, too.
Why did I let her talk me
into coming out here to ski?
[MIKU]
What is it I'm trying to do?
Okay, so,
how are we gonna escape?
Let's see.
I know.
Yotsuba should have
a handicap.
[FUTARO]
What?
We could make her carry
a bunch of stuff.
That way,
she can't move as fast.
Hah. That might
make it more fun.
Yeah. Great!
But I'm not sure
if I like that idea.
You five were born with
the exact same characteristics
and abilities, right?
You're quintuplets.
That means Yotsuba's
the most athletic one
because she worked hard
to earn that for herself.
I guess that makes sense.
I know this is just
a stupid game of tag, but...
I still don't want
to disrespect her effort.
[MAEDA] You do it because
you want that person
all to yourself.
[ICHIKA] Are you sure
you're okay with that?
[MIKU]
It's fine if he's with Ichika.
[ITSUKI]
What were you guys doing?
[MIKU]
But I can't.
It's only fair
for you to dance with him.
It's good that
you're all equals,
but you can't ignore
the work she's done, either.
♪
You should be fair
instead of equal.
♪
[grunts]
[groans]
Uh, you good?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What is wrong with you?
♪
You're right.
We should be fair.
Huh?
Jeez, what am I sitting here
rambling about?
The heat's making me crazy.
I'll go get some fresh air.
♪
[giggles]
Uesugi?
I'm gonna find you,
no matter what!
♪
[sighs]
Where did he run off to?
Kintaro.
[wind whooshing]
♪
[cell phone buzzing]
Hey there, Miku.
What's going on?
Ichika. Listen.
There's something I need to say.
-[ITSUKI] Futaro.
-[NINO] Get up, Uesugi!
[MIKU]
Futaro.
[YOTSUBA]
Uesugi!
[ICHIKA]
Wake up, Uesugi.
[FUTARO] A-ha! I never
actually met the quintuplets.
This was all a dream!
[QUINTUPLETS]
You know that's not true!