[bell ringing]
[FUTARO]
I was having a dream...
[WOMAN]
Please wake up now, sir.
Your bride is ready
and waiting for you.
[FUTARO groans]
[FUTARO]
A dream about
the incredible day
that brought us together.
One barbecue combo.
And hold the barbecue.
[LUNCH LADY]
Comin' up.
[FUTARO]
You'd think the cheapest thing
on the cafeteria menu
would be rice, but it's not.
You save 200 yen if you skip
the beef in the combo.
It's rice, soup, and veggies
for the same cost as just rice.
[FUTARO]
And the water's free!
I love this place.
Eating alone, as always. Heh.
That loser!
[FUTARO]
Hmph.
Uh.
Huh?
[gasps]
[STUDENT A]
Hey, who's that girl?
[STUDENT AA]
She's sitting with Uesugi?
[STUDENT B]
No one does that!
[FUTARO]
That's not our uniform.
Wait, how did this happen?
[ITSUKI] I found this
spot before you did.
The next table is wide open.
I think you should move.
This is the table
that I sit at every day!
Why don't you move?
[ITSUKI gasps]
[STUDENT BB] Look, Uesugi's
eating lunch with a girl!
Is she stupid?
Tch. Seriously?
[FUTARO]
She's all red.
You could've switched seats.
[FUTARO gasps]
[FUTARO]
250 for udon.
Two shrimp tempura
would be 300.
The other varieties of tempura
cost a 100 yen each.
Add the pudding and that's--
Who just drops a
thousand yen on lunch?!
Well, you do you.
Time to eat.
Uh?
[ITSUKI] That's a little rude,
don't you think?
You're studying
in the middle of lunch?
I'm reviewing my exam.
Leave me alone, jeez.
Wow, you must have gotten
a pretty rotten grade, huh?
Can I take a look?
Ah! Hey!
Let's see, Mr. Futaro Uesugi.
You scored a--
[gasps]
[ITSUKI]
A... hundred?
Is this real?
Oh, no! I'm so embarrassed!
You wanted me to see it!
[ITSUKI] I hate to admit it, but
I'm not good at school stuff.
I envy you.
You know, it must've been fate
that brought us together!
Do you wanna help me study?
Well, this has been great.
Uh! You're already done?
You didn't eat much.
Are you sure you got enough?
If you want more,
I'd be happy to share mine.
If anything, you ordered
way too much food.
Don't get fat.
What the--?!
I think you might be
the most insensitive person
--I've met in my entire life!
--[phone ringing]
I'm not sharing
anything with you!
[FUTARO]
A chance to pay off our debt?
[RAIHA] Yeah, Dad found
a part-time job for you.
A super-rich family
just moved here.
They're looking to hire a tutor.
What do you think?
[FUTARO]
A tutor, huh?
You would get to work
in a nice fancy house.
And it pays five times
the going rate.
[FUTARO]
That sounds like a sketchy deal
if I'm being honest.
Well, selling a kidney
is sketchy, too,
but you only need one to live.
Whoa, what are you suggesting?
[RAIHA laughs]
[RAIHA]
It's a joke.
But if you do do it,
then you'll be able to afford
some actual meals.
It's worth a try.
[stomach growls]
[FUTARO] So, do we know anything
about who I'm tutoring?
[RAIHA]
Hmm... High school age?
In fact, I'm pretty sure he said
you were gonna be classmates.
What was the name? Nakano?
Itsuki Nakano.
It's so nice to meet all of you.
[gasps]
[FUTARO]
This chick again?!
--A new girl!
--[STUDENT C] And she's cute!
Hey, that's the Kurobara
uniform, isn't it?
[STUDENT D]
Her folks must be loaded!
[FUTARO]
A rich transfer student?
Obviously, it's her.
Uh... Hey...
[ITSUKI]
Hmph.
You mind if I sit here?
[FUTARO]
Great... Just great.
[LUNCH LADY]
Here's that barbecue beef combo,
hold the beef.
[FUTURO]
Yesterday didn't go too well.
But if she rejects me again,
then I'll lose the job
of a lifetime!
I have to get back
on her good side.
[FUTARO]
Hello again.
Could I have the honor
of dining with you today?
And of course, I'd be happy
to help with your studies.
[ITSUKI]
Wow!
[FUTARO]
It's foolproof!
[gasps]
Hey, sorry I'm late.
[FUTARO]
She's eating with... friends?!
[ITSUKI gasps]
Oops, it looks like we don't
have any room left for you.
[FUTARO]
Mm-hmm...
[ICHIKA]
Hey, wait! Don't just leave!
Huh?
[ICHIKA] You're after Itsuki,
aren't you? Hmm?
Uh, I'm not after her.
Oh? So she is
the one that you like!
[ICHIKA giggles]
So what is it about her
you're attracted to?
Let me guess:
It's her serious side!
I know! I'll go tell
her to come over!
[FUTARO]
No.
[gasps]
I don't need anyone's help.
My problems are mine
alone to solve.
[ICHIKA giggles]
Wow, that was so manly!
You know, for a nerd.
But if you ever do need help,
you can just ask
your Big Sis Ichika.
This is gonna be fun.
Hold on, "Big Sis"?
We're the same year, aren't we?
[FUTARO]
This is no good.
I'm supposed to meet
that bratty girl
as her tutor today after school.
--[YOTSUBA] Uesugi? 'Scuse me?
--[FUTARO] What now?
[YOTSUBA]
Hey, Uesugi!
[giggles]
You finally looked up.
[FUTARO]
Whoa! Who the heck are you?
And how do you know
what my name is?
[YOTSUBA laughs]
[YOTSUB] Those are both
excellent questions!
Did you lose an exam paper
with a perfect score?
Or perhaps one
with a zero score?
You have my exam? But how?
Well, it's a long story.
[YOTSUBA]
Earlier...
...that happened.
And then, I noticed it.
And now, here we are!
So, which one is yours?
[FUTARO]
This one.
Wow! You're such an honest guy!
I'll give you both as a reward!
[FUTARO]
That's okay.
What idiot got a zero?
You're lookin' right at her!
[FUTARO] And you're not
even embarrassed?!
[YOTSUBA] You know,
when I first saw you,
I thought you were nothin'
but a grumpy, boring old loner.
Now I know that you're all that
and a super-genius!
That was quick!
[BOYS]
Uh...
[grunting]
Are you still following me?!
Well, yeah, you haven't
said "thank you" yet.
What?!
[YOTSUBA] When someone
picks up your stuff,
you thank them.
You'd think a super-genius
would know something like that.
[FUTARO]
Here, I picked this up for you.
Now, we're even.
Yeah! Thanks so much
for your help!
[FUTARO]
Don't thank me for that!
I don't know why I thought
she'd walk home by herself.
[NINO]
Itsuki, aren't you eating a lot?
It's not that much.
This is only my second one.
[NINO]
Look out, it's the bun monster!
Ah! Hey, get off of my case!
[NINO] You're gonna
scare the boys away!
[ITSUKI]
Mind your own business!
When am I gonna apologize?
[MIKU]
Is it fun being alone?
Uh...
Uh, it's not bad.
This is my hobby.
[MIKU]
I see.
Staring at girls
is your hobby, huh?
Just a second.
Please don't
call the cops on me.
And please don't tell
your friend Itsuki about this.
Fine, I won't.
Also, that girl is
in no way my friend.
[FUTARO]
Huh?
[groans]
[FUTARO]
She lives here?
How rich can one person be?
But this is it.
At least, I think it is.
[crashing]
[grunts]
[NINO] What are you,
some kind of stalker?
State your name and
business, or get lost.
My business has nothing
to do with you.
I'll decide that.
Listen, nobody likes you.
So go home already, scum!
[FUTARO]
I'd love to.
But this building is my home.
[ITSUKI]
Uh, really? I'm sorry!
One barbecue beef combo,
hold the barbecue.
Huh?!
[MIKU]
Are you on a diet?
Huh?
Uh! Hey, you!
I knew it!
[FUTARO]
Found her!
This is my last
chance to fix it!
[FUTARO grunts]
[FUTARo]
Please don't close!
[FUTARO groans]
[yelling]
[FUTARO]
This whole thing is her fault!
I shouldn't have to apologize
for any of this crap!
It's her fault that I'm tired
and sweaty from running.
It's her fault that those
weirdos keep harassing me.
It's all...
[gasps]
[FUTARO]
...it's all her... fault.
Hey, you're that guy
from school.
What could be so important
that you would follow me
all the way home?
[FUTARO]
About yesterday...
Huh? Yesterday?
What are you even
doing here, anyway?
I told you. You see, I-I was--
Never mind, I don't care.
Wait, listen to me!
No, you listen! You're starting
to get on my nerves!
I have a meeting with my
tutor in a few minutes,
so if could you
please leave alre--
That'd be me.
What?!
[FUTARO]
Your new tutor. It's me.
Gah!
[ITSUKI gasps]
No way, I refuse!
[FUTARO]
I hate it, too!
Much more than you do!
But... I'm still
not gonna give up.
Yesterday, I was totally in
the wrong, and I'm sorry.
But that changes now!
Starting today...
I'm your partner!
[ITSUKI]
This can't be right.
It's not fair!
Why does our tutor have
to be you, of all people?
[FUTARO]
Did you say "our"?
[ICHIKA] I can't believe
there was a creeper
hanging around
outside our condo!
--[YOTSUBA] Whoa!
--[NINO] Scary!
[gasps]
Huh?!
Hey there, Mr. Honor Roll!
That's him, he's the stalker!
Uesugi's a stalker?!
Don't assume things.
[FUTARO]
Why are you all here?!
[ITSUKI sighs]
'Cause this is where
we live, obviously.
[FUTARO]
Uh...
Oh, I see. You share a fancy
condo with all your girlfriends.
[FUTARO] My poor brain,
under heavy duress
and overclocked past
its manufacturer limit,
reached the only
logical conclusion
that it could possibly muster.
A dream. This is
definitely a dream.
[ITSUKI] We're not friends,
we're sisters.
[gulps]
In fact, we're quintuplets.
[FUTARO]
My name is Futaro Uesugi,
and I'll be your tutor
starting today.
Let's all make studying
fun, and, uh...
What the hell?!
Why is nobody in here?!
Hey, hey! Sorry I'm late!
Oh, uh...
You're the one with
the zero. Yotsuba.
[YOTSUBA chuckles nervously]
Could you do me a quick
favor and scowl at me?
Uh... What, like this?
[FUTARO]
Yup, they're related.
So, why are you here?
Obviously, it's time to start
our first tutoring session.
Where else would I be?!
Thank you, Yotsuba.
Please, let me hug you.
Well! Let's go and round up
the other girls, shall we?
All of our bedrooms
are side-by-side, see?
Itsuki, me, that one's Miku,
then Nino, and Ichika's
at the end.
Great. This is gonna
be such a pain.
Oh, no, it'll be easy!
Itsuki is a real
serious student!
She'll cooperate as long as
you don't make her too angry!
[ITSUKI]
Not a chance.
What's the point of a tutor
who's in the same class as I am?
There has to be someone
in this city
better qualified
for the position than you are.
What gives?
Yesterday, you wanted
me to help you!
Well, I was wrong.
It's not happening.
[YOTSUBA giggles nervously]
With five of us,
there's bound to be
at least one disagreement.
Miku's the smartest one here.
She'll come down.
I'm sure you'll get
along fine with her.
No.
Honestly, why does
it have to be you?
There has to be someone
in this city better--
[FUTARO]
Yup, I've heard that already.
Um, maybe we should move on?
Nino can hit it off with
anybody, so you'll be fine!
She's like a social butterfly!
Uh, but I guess
she stepped out?
Uh, you don't need
to worry, though!
We still gotta go see Ichika!
She's really...
Uh...
[FUTARO]
What's with the pause?
[YOTSUBA]
Don't freak out, okay?
[FUTARO gasps]
It's like some kind
of disaster area!
An actual human lives in here?
[ICHIKA]
Stop talking about my room
like it's this disgusting
wasteland full of toxic sludge.
[YOTSUBA]
Ugh, this place is a wreck!
[ICHIKA]
Wow, I wasn't expecting you
to be our mysterious new tutor.
That's why you
were after Itsuki.
Forget that. Come on,
let's go downstairs.
Whoa! That's a bad idea!
[gasps]
[ICHIKA giggles]
[ICHIKA]
I'm kinda naked here.
[FUTARO]
Wha--? But why?
[ICHIKA]
Yotsuba?
There should be some clothes
near your feet somewhere.
[YOTSUBA]
Uh, let's see.
[FUTARO]
Good grief.
When was the last time you
used this desk for studying?
[ICHIKA] Ugh! Studying
this, studying that.
I hope you're not always this
concerned about your schoolwork
when you're in a bedroom
with a cute, naked girl.
--[FUTARO] Ugh...
--Here we go!
Just get dressed and come to the
living room when you're done.
Honestly...
What was your name again?
Futaro? I have a question.
[FUTARO]
Huh?
It seems I'm missing
part of my P.E. uniform.
A red track jacket.
That's too bad.
I haven't seen it.
[MIKU]
It was here before.
Right up until you came in.
Did you--?
No!
[NINO]
Hey!
I made way too many
cookies. Want some?
[FUTARO] Good, at least
I've got four of you here.
Well! Time to hit the--
[ICHICKA]
Ooh, yum!
What flavor is this?
[MIKU] Why are you wearing
my track jacket?
[NINO] I was baking and I didn't
wanna get my outfit dirty.
Take it off right now.
[NINO]
Hey, let go of me!
[MIKU]
Give it back!
[NINO] You can have it
later, calm down!
[YOTSUBA]
Uesugi!
Don't worry about me!
I'm already studying hard!
[FUTARO groans]
[NINO] It's Saturday, we should
go somewhere fun!
Oh, did I get a package?
[FUTARO]
They're hopeless!
What am I supposed
to do with them?!
[NINO]
You don't like cookies?
Uh? No, I'm just
not in the mood.
You don't have
to be so nervous.
It's not like
I poisoned them, you know.
Have some and I'll study with
you, does that sound good?
[FUTARO grunts]
[NINO] Wow! You're really
scarfing them down!
You like them?
Yeah! They're awesome!
Aw, thanks!
Oh, there's something
I meant to tell you!
None of us need a tutor,
so you should probably go away.
[MIKU]
Uh.
I was just kidding!
Here, have some water.
Uh, good idea, thank you.
[FUTARO] Damn. I'm not surprised
that they're slacking off.
But they need to graduate!
For their sake... and mine.
Well, goodbye!
Huh?
[DRIVER] Sir? Pardon me,
but we've arrived, sir.
[groans]
Huh?
Huh?!
Wait, where--?
What's wrong?
This is your home, isn't it?
[FUTARO]
Well, it is, but how did I..."
--[NINO giggles]
--[FUTARO gasps]
[FUTARO]
It was her!
[DRIVER]
4800 yen, please.
Uh! That much?!
I don't have it!
[ITSUKI]
Here you go.
[DRIVER]
Ah. Thank you, miss.
[FUTARO gasps]
[FUTARO]
Itsuki!
[ITSUKI] I got your address
from your student handbook.
[FUTARO]
Uh... Uh?
Did you look at the photo?
[ITSUKI]
What're you talking about?
Anyway, you can't
win against us.
You're a smart guy,
so I hope you're bright enough
to give up on tutoring us.
Sorry, but I can't.
[ITSUKI gasps]
Don't be stubborn!
[RAIHA giggles]
[RAIHA]
You're back, Big Brother!
Hey, Raiha.
I'm so glad you're home!
Let's eat dinner!
Huh?
Wow!
Wow, is she your new student?
[FUTARO]
Uh, she's nobody.
Just go back inside.
[RAIHA]
Don't lie to me!
Excuse me, miss!
Would you like to have
dinner at our house?
[ITSUKI gasps]
[FUTARO]
Raiha!
What'd I do?
You don't... want to?
[gasps]
[RAIHA]
Ta-da!
It’s the Uesugi special:
Curry and rolled egg!
I hope everything
turned out okay!
[ITSUKI]
It looks delicious!
Ahhh!
Sure you can stomach this
commoner food, princess?
[ITSUKI grunbles]
[FUTARO yelps]
--Hey!
--[RAIHA] Jeez!
[ISANARI laughs]
And that's why you'll never be
as popular as your old man is.
[FUTARO]
Dad.
[ISANARI]
I gotta say, I didn't think
I'd live to see the day
you brought a girl home!
So, Big Brother?
[FUTARO]
Huh?
[RAIHA] How was
your first day of tutoring?
[BOTH gasp]
Well, actually, he--
Of course everything
went perfectly!
Why'd you say that?
Just lie. Don't make her sad.
What's wrong?
[FUTARO]
Huh?! Nothing!
[ITSUKI]
Yeah! Everything's great!
Ah... I'm so happy to hear that.
Maybe now we can finally
take care of all our debt.
[FUTARO] Not in front
of the guest, Raiha.
[RAIHA]
Oh, sorry.
[ITSUKI]
Thanks for the meal.
[ISANARI]
Sure.
You, too. It was lovely. Huh?
[RAIHA]
Itsuki?
[ITSUKI]
Yes?
I know my big brother's
a stuck-up scumbag loser jerk
and everything...
Uh, hey...
[RAIHA]
...but he's good in some ways.
[gasps]
What I wanna say is...
...will you come here
again sometime?
[chuckles]
[ITSUKI]
Of course I will!
Using my brain
makes me super hungry!
I'm looking forward
to the next time!
[ITSUKI]
Don't get the wrong idea.
I may know what
your situation is like now,
but I still can't help you.
[FUTARO]
Is that so?
I'll study hard whether
you tutor me or not.
I can accomplish my goals
with or without you.
It's your choice.
So if you want to be our tutor,
then you can go right ahead.
[gasps]
What did you say?
What? I just said
it's your choice.
Wow, you really mean that?
I can keep the job?!
Thank you, Itsuki!
Uh, sure?
[FUTARO] I'll be there
tomorrow at noon sharp!
Tell your sisters to be ready!
[ITSUKI]
Uh-huh.
[FUTARO]
That's right,
my only job is to make sure
the five of them graduate.
That doesn't mean I actually
have to deal with all five
and their annoyink
I just need to teach the ones
who are at risk of failing.
Do you think Futaro knows?
I highly doubt he does.
[ICHIKA] It's not like anybody
would've told him
that we transferred here
because all five of us
almost flunked out.
[bells ringing]
Yeah, you're right.
[FUTARO]
All these years later,
I still relive that moment
in my dreams.
[FUTARO]
Or should I say...
...my nightmares...
[ITSUKI]
Quintuplets Trivia!
[NINO] Altogether, we weigh
about 250 kilograms!
[ITSUKI] Hey, that divides
evenly by five!
50 kilos each,
the average weight
for a healthy young girl!
Let's leave it at that!
[YOTSUBA]
Uh, but--
[ITSUKI]
I said leave it at that!
[MIKU, YOTSUBA]
Fine.