[intro music playing]
[bell ringing]
[whimpering]
-Run away, Ichiru.
YUKI: Not too many
people here today.
-That's because the
exams are tomorrow.
-Oh!
That's right!
-Oh!!
-The class with
the lowest student
test scores will end
up having to work
during the ball this year.
-You really want to go, huh?
-Huh?
Not really.
I mean, we have our
disciplinary committee duties,
BOY: If I don't get to
dance with Ruka this year,
I'll hold a grudge
against you for life!
-And the class rep will be
so fussy about everything,
so I was just trying to figure
out the best thing for me
to do.
[door creaking]
-It's so quiet.
I wish it were like
this all the time.
You still concerned?
-I'm not the only one.
HANABUSA: You are
the only one who
would know-- because-- you
have-- a blood bond with her.
-Zero!
[giggles]
YUKI: Hey, what's going on?
ZERO: I told you.
Stay away from that
transfer student.
-Yeah, I know.
But why?
-It doesn't matter.
Just whatever you do, don't
get involved with her.
I beg you.
[theme music playing]
[guitar music playing]
-Zero.
Why was he so
adamant about Maria?
KAIEN: Hey!
Yuki!
You're daydreaming again.
Focus!
-Huh?
I'm so sorry.
-Like I said, you substitute
the value for x over there,
and then--
YUKI: What?
Why?
KAIEN: You don't know why?
Oh, Zero, perfect timing.
Would you tutor Yuki for me?
The exams are tomorrow, and
I'm afraid that she still
doesn't get it.
Perhaps you could help.
-Sure, no problem.
KAIEN: Then I'll
leave it to you.
It's my duty to go on
patrol during exam time.
By the way, Zero, did you want
to see me about something?
Is that why you
came here tonight?
-No.
It's no big deal.
-OK.
[clock ticking]
-You realize you made the same
sort of mistake last time?
You have to be more careful.
-Huh?
Oh wow.
You're right.
OK.
Then this number goes here,
and then use these numbers here
to get the total value.
Is that right?
-Yes, it is.
[clock ticking]
-Is something wrong?
Your neck bothering you?
-The wound that woman
made has been-- throbbing.
-Every single night I remember.
Four years ago.
She toyed with my brother
and me in the blood bath.
But I think I've been
able to keep living.
[chair moving]
-Come on, now, Zero.
You're not acting like
your usual self today.
What's wrong?
How about we take a break now?
I'll make some coffee, OK?
[foot steps]
-Come on, Zero.
What's wrong?
KANAME: That body.
That name.
At first, I was puzzled
at how to respond.
-I was only trying
to not embarrass you.
-Well, it was offensive.
It was obvious that you were
just playing around with us.
-Me play a game?
This is interesting.
Tell me, when did you
decide to grow up and start
looking at things
so conscientiously?
We are both Purebloods.
[giggling]
[footsteps]
[door closing]
-Do you-- want my blood?
-I think I was able to live
on because you were beside me.
-Zero.
-I'm going back to my dorm now.
Don't forget our lesson.
-OK.
I won't.
Hey, thanks for tutoring me.
Good night, Zero.
-Good night.
-Something is on
Zero's mind today.
-But is it just today?
No.
It's been since--
[gasping]
-Since Maria came.
[running]
-What does Maria mean to Zero?
[string music playing]
[door creaking]
[foot steps]
-That's right.
You have the ability
to sense my presence.
Because there is
a bond between us.
It feels the
emptiness in my heart.
-Finally, you've
come to kill me.
Go ahead, and punish
me for my sins, Zero.
Providing you can
actually pull the trigger.
-Are you surprised?
That you can't do it?
-Don't touch me!
-You are incapable
of killing me.
I am your master.
I gave you life as a vampire.
You are my faithful servant.
You can't kill me.
[gasping]
-You are the first who
hasn't yielded to me.
Such a good boy.
You make me so incredibly happy.
You figured out who I am, Zero,
even if I look different now.
You knew I was the one who
took your life as a human.
-That's right.
I can't forget.
Shizuka Hio.
That day, your true face
was covered with our blood.
YUKI: I don't believe it.
Maria is the vampire who
pushed Zero into the darkness?
MARIA: As you know,
this body isn't mine,
so I want you to treat
it as gently as you can.
-Zero!
WOMAN: Don't you dare!
Look away!
[gun shot]
MARIA: A borrowed body can
be a little difficult to use.
Once our wounds heal, we're back
where we started, aren't we?
-What are you--
[groaning]
-As you can see, a large loss of
blood can cause intense hunger.
Be careful.
A vampire's true self is
extremely savage and cruel.
However, vampire hunters
are very similar.
If you ask me.
Now, take him out of here.
-So you're going
to let him live?
[foot steps]
KANAME: If something like this
kills him, he is of no use
at all.
However, you are the one that
I just cannot bear to lose.
-What was I doing?
[bell ringing]
GIRL: How do I do this?
I feel asleep last night!
CLASS REP: Listen up, everyone!
You have to score
high in every subject!
Is that understood?
[people talking]
[ticking]
-Why is Lord Kaname
visiting that girl?
-Just calm down.
I'm sure he's meeting
about the ball.
He's only going to talk to
the disciplinary committee.
-I know, but I
can tell that he--
[bells ringing]
YUKI: It's over at last!
GIRL: How'd you do?
-Aced it!
-Finally, it's all over.
Hey!
How about we go into
town to that tea room?
Huh, Yuki?
-Huh?
Oh, sure.
[people talking]
GIRL: Yuki.
Yuki.
Are you all right?
You don't look that well.
Maybe you should go
home and rest instead.
-Yeah, you're right.
Good idea.
I'm sorry.
I wonder what is wrong with me.
[girls gasping and screaming]
KANAME: Good afternoon, Yuki.
YUKI: Kaname.
[girls talking]
GIRL: Hey!
Don't push me!
-Hi!
[girls screaming]
YUKI: Is something wrong?
I mean, now is--
KANAME: I wanted to
discuss the ball with you.
-Oh, OK.
-I'll see you there, won't I?
-That's right.
I've been asked to
patrol the ballroom.
-That's not what I mean.
-But, I really don't have
anything to wear to something
like that, and I also have
my duties to attend to, so--
-When we were kids, we used to
dance together all the time.
-Huh?
Yeah.
That's right.
I was always so bad at it,
and you would try to guide me.
-You would charge
blindly ahead back then.
I wanted to be near you at
all times to protect you.
I don't want to
see you get hurt.
-Kaname.
[feet shuffling]
KANAME: Don't worry.
I will always be with you.
-Um, Kaname!
We should really get going now.
-Right.
Well then, I will
see you at the ball.
-Um, right.
-See you later, Yuki.
-Looks like she doesn't
remember anything.
-Some things are
better forgotten.
[foot steps]
-I can smell it.
Smells like trouble.
Just what do you
think you're doing?
KAIEN: You think so, huh?
I happen to have an
affinity for this smell.
It's delicious.
YAGARI: Why would you allow
her to come here at all?
-It was Kaname's recommendation.
The vampire world
has its own rules
and ways of dealing with things.
We just have to
let them handle it.
-Are you treating Zero like
he's a vampire just like them?
Hey!
[sighing]
[door opening]
[door closing]
[cat mewing]
-What's wrong?
Did you get lost somehow?
-You're so cold.
-Huh?
-Aren't you, Yuki?
-Maria.
-How could you have
forgotten that boy
when he clearly thinks
so much about you?
YUKI: That boy?
-Wherever you go, he's
always by your side.
-Who do you mean?
You mean Zero?
[cat growling]
[gasping]
-I remember.
Why had I forgotten?
[giggling]
-(GASPING) Hold on!
Maria, wait!
What did you do to Zero?
-He's going to be all
right for the time being.
But sooner or later, he
will become a Level E.
And when that happens, he
won't listen to you anymore.
However, if you're interested,
there is a way to save him.
Let's make a deal.
I want you to do something
that only you can do.
[bell ringing]
[groaning]
-Zero!
-Ichiru.
You've got a fever.
You should be in bed.
-I lied about being sick, Zero.
But you knew that.
-You didn't want to be
here to see off the master?
Why not, Ichiru?
-I'm a drop out anyway, so I'm
of no use to a guy like him.
It's a waste of
time for us both.
He doesn't take me
seriously to begin with.
But I'm fine with it.
I only need your love, Zero.
[chimes]
-Is that snow?
-No.
The cherry blossoms are
blooming out of season.
[music playing]
-She's so beautiful.
-Zero?
-Ichiru, it's time
we head back home.
Father and Mother are
probably looking for us.
-What's wrong, Zero?
-That woman there is a vampire.
-(GROANING) You could sense
it, but I couldn't tell.
-Ichiru?
-Zero, you're really amazing.
You make up for
the things I lack.
-Ichiru.
-Ichiru, you-- you have a fever.
Probably from being
out in the cold.
-Look at this.
I knew it.
He snuck into your bed
again, Zero, didn't he?
So tell me, how is
he feeling tonight?
-Mother, he has a fever.
I'll go run and get an ice
pack if you'll just stay here
with Ichiru until
I get back, OK?
ICHIRU: Don't go, Zero.
-I'll go get it for him.
Zero, you look after Ichiru.
He really loves you, Zero.
ICHIRU: Being so
frail like this,
I'll never become a hunter.
Hey, Zero, that
vampire we saw today.
Will Father or Mother or
perhaps even some other hunter
go after her and kill her?
-Who knows?
But if it's on the list,
someone will hunt it.
-Zero, I know you
and I are both being
trained to hunt
vampires some day,
but will you be able to kill?
You're such a kind person.
-Listen, don't worry
about me, Ichiru.
That's why the Master's
teachings are so important.
-You sound as if you think
it's your duty, Zero,
but I realize that what you're
really trying to do is make up
for me to--
-No, I'm not, Ichiru.
[wind blowing]
MOTHER: Where's Ichiru?
ZERO: He should be back soon.
[gasping]
-Hey, Zero, what is it?
[bell ringing]
-A vampire is burying
its fangs right now.
Ichiru!
-Zero!
[door opening]
-Clever boy.
You knew I was here even
before your parents noticed.
The twin children
of the hunters.
It all comes down to
your sinful blood.
-What are you talking about?
[bell ringing]
-I will further curse your
fate, child of the hunters.
FATHER: Zero!
Zero!
Shizuka, heel.
-Heel?
FATHER: What does a Pureblood
vampire want from us?
SHIZUKA: You killed him.
So now, I will punish you.
FATHER: No!
-Zero!
No!
[groaning]
ZERO: Ichiru!
Run away!
If you do anything to
Ichiru, I will kill you!
-That's a really terrible mask.
Is that her doing?
Will you take it off?
Don't wear it in front of me.
I thought you were dead.
[laughs]
ZERO: Ichiru.
[credit music playing]