[theme music]
[gun shots]
ZERO: When did this
happened to us?
I hope what you're
trying to protect
doesn't end up
causing you more pain.
[gasping]
-How long you intend
to stand there?
YUKI: Well, I'm
worried about you.
I wanted to know if
you're really OK.
-It's not easy.
Being my nursemaid, is it?
-Come on, Zero.
Are you OK?
[gun shots]
-Guess you're better than OK.
-Yuki, take that
gauze off your neck.
It's way too obvious.
-No!
I have to wear this thing.
If I only wear a
band-aid then I'll
have people like Aido just
come up to me and peel it off!
(QUIETLY) And, if someone
were to actually see it--
ZERO: Someone like Kaname.
[gasping]
ZERO: If you were going to
have someone drink your blood,
your preference probably would
have been Kaname Kuran over me,
wouldn't it?
-Huh?
-It wasn't that hard to tell.
Your blood-- it had
that taste to it.
-Ugh!
Stop!
That's sick!
Don't say things like that!
It's like you're peeking
inside me, and I hate it!
[theme music]
[heavy breathing]
-I don't need him to remind me.
What Kaname's
existence means to me.
I know it more than anyone else.
And yet, what I
did to Kaname was--
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Will
you commit betrayal?
Just cover your eyes.
Pretend you know nothing.
-But-- But I--
CHILD (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
Scary vampires will eat me.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER):
Innocence is a sin.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Turn
your eyes from the truth,
not realizing how foolish it is.
CHILD (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
KAIEN: Yes.
Of course, I can look
after this child.
You're the surviving son of
the person who I owe a lot to.
(SIGHING) She doesn't
even understand
that the pudding is food.
-Yes.
She seems to have
lost all her memories.
You scoop it up with
a spoon like this.
Here.
Now say, ah.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): The
truth cannot be changed.
-What's wrong?
Just open wide.
[whimpering]
-Sorry, but I think
it's best if I leave now
and never see her
again after all.
I'll go home.
-Go back home?
To that place?
There's nothing but a den of
monsters waiting for you there,
and all they want is to
take advantage of you
since your parents
have passed away.
-Yes.
But I have no choice.
You take care.
[music playing]
KAIEN: That person said to me
that girls are born princesses.
So from today, I'll
give you a name
that means tender princess.
You'll be Yuki.
Is that OK?
Do you see something outside?
It's all right.
If you stay here, you'll
be perfectly safe.
[chimes]
KAIEN: Yuki!
I filed all the papers
to legally adopt you!
So as of today, I'm
officially your father!
Come on, let's hear
it, call me father!
It's been over a week, and
you haven't said a word to me.
You're starting to
make me insecure.
I don't know what to do.
Huh?
Yuki?
KANAME: You said you
were having trouble
with her, so I shook off my
guard and rushed over here.
But I take it, you lied.
That's it.
How can I ever trust you again?
KAIEN: Please.
Just go and see her.
Oh!
Kaname!
Come here!
You have to see this!
KANAME: What happened?
-Yuki dressed herself
for the first time ever!
Although, it's not quite right.
Kaname?
[laughing]
-Ooh!
What should I do?
Kaname has gone berserk!
[laughing]
-Huh?
-If I can scared you, I'm sorry.
-Oh.
-All right, I must go.
Bye-bye.
YUKI: Kana- me.
Kaname.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER):
Peaceful, gentle moments.
That is the hope and sin.
KAIEN: Yuki?
Wait inside!
You'll freeze out there!
-Ah! (GIGGLING) Lord Kaname!
-You said, "Lord."
What for?
-Do you know what today is?
It's my birthday!
It's been one year
from the day you
rescued me and saved my life.
Congratulations, Lord Kaname.
-Actually, Yuki.
Today is the day we
congratulate you.
But, thanks anyway.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER):
A deceiving heart.
Overflowing with kindness.
Sins-- piled on top of sins.
-Kaname is a--
vampire, isn't he?
-Yes.
But unfortunately,
our government
doesn't officially
acknowledge vampires exist.
So you have to keep it
a secret, too, Yuki.
-Really?
It's a secret?
But then, Kaname--
he was so nice
when he let me touch
his vampire fangs.
He's different.
Kaname is nothing like
that scary vampire was.
-Have you ever once
seen Kaname do something
you didn't want him to do, Yuki?
See, he's proof that there are
friendly vampires out there,
too.
-(LAUGHING) Yeah.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): A
special day of the season.
A rendez-vous approved,
but with boundaries.
A moment of happiness,
and the fading truth.
-If he's visiting
us, then he would
have to pass through
here on his way.
Kaname still isn't here,
and it's getting dark.
[gasping]
CHILD (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
Scary vampires will eat me!
-Yuki.
-Kaname!
-I thought you were
afraid to walk around town
all by yourself.
-If you're with me, then
I'm not scared of anything!
KANAME: And neither am I.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER):
Innocence is a sin.
The truth cannot be changed.
Time will wait for no one.
KAIEN: Yuki!
Sorry I'm late.
His name is Zero Kiryu.
Take care of him, Yuki.
His family was killed
by a bad vampire.
[gasping]
[music playing]
[heart beat]
-Zero?
Wha-
[heart beat]
[gun shot]
[groaning]
YUKI: Zero?
What are-- you doing?
-It's disgusting.
It's still there.
I still feel that woman's touch.
-Zero, stop!
That has to hurt!
You're talking about
that vampire who
did horrible things to
your family, aren't you?
And-- she did awful
things to you, too.
But-- it's all okay now.
-Huh?
YUKI: I'll always be with
you, so you'll be all right.
YUKI: It's like you're peeking
inside me, and I hate it!
KAIEN: Zero, when you see,
I think you'll understand.
-I think you'll understand.
-Understand what?
-Come on, hurry, come in!
Weren't you cold out there?
(GIGGLING) Kaname.
Kaname, guess what!
KANAME: What is it?
[giggling]
[gasping]
[music playing]
-No!
Zero, don't!
-Vampire!
-Kaname!
-You just ran up and
stabbed me for no reason.
That isn't nice.
-Shut up, Vampire!
I know what you are!
You have the same
smell as that woman!
-That woman?
Then you must be Zero Kiryu.
I'm very sorry for what
happened to your family,
but I do not intend to stand
here and let you kill me
either.
KAIEN: Zero, he's not the one
who warrants your revenge.
YUKI: Zero, I'm sorry.
I should have told
you about him sooner.
You OK?
Zero?
-Don't touch me!
With those hands
that touched him!
-But Kaname is
someone who rescued me
when I was about to be
eaten by a scary vampire.
He's a kind vampire.
ZERO: There's something's
wrong with both you
and the headmaster.
KAIEN: I'm going to establish
a night class at our school.
-Do you mean like an evening
class for the seniors?
No,
-It's not for the high school
or university students.
The classes will run at night,
and most of their studies
will be high level
research, and they
won't receive grades either.
You see, these are
nocturnal students
who live much longer lives.
We can't treat them like us.
Every student in the night
class is going to be a vampire.
ZERO: What are you trying to do?
Letting those things
in the school.
KANAME: The goal is to
promote peaceful coexistence
between vampires and humans.
And to educate young
vampires, so they
become a politically
moderate force.
That his plan.
-Kaname Kuran.
-Kaname!
-Good evening, Yuki.
-Huh?
-That's absurd.
There's no way
that vampires want
to peacefully
coexist with humans.
Their history is
stained with the blood
of innocent people's lives.
-And it is our goal
to put an end to that.
I know how you must feel, Zero.
I, too, have lost
someone because of them.
-Then why?
KAIEN: There's no need to worry.
Kaname has agreed to join
the night class as well.
This will ensure that the
other vampires behave.
-But, things are over
if he double-crosses us.
-He wasn't the one who
proved to be a traitor.
KAIEN: Kaname, it
makes me very happy
that you've chosen to
support my pacifist views.
KANAME: Yes, I hope your
views can become a reality.
And since I'll be bound
by certain restrictions,
I'll appreciate the students
who can move at my beckon call.
However, one thing
still concerns me.
-Yuki.
[music playing]
-I won't regret it,
that's what I thought.
ZERO: Your blood-- It
had that taste to it.
-Can a vampire do that?
Can they know someone's feelings
just by tasting their blood?
-When did you stop talking
to me about everything, Yuki?
-When?
Yes, it was that day.
That's when something changed.
YUKI: The teacher's dorm.
It isn't being used by
anyone right now, is it?
-It's being used
as a temporary dorm
until the entrance exams
and pledges are completed.
It's for the vampires.
Stay away from their lair, Yuki.
-Then-- Kaname is there, too.
-Yah.
-Oh, it's you, Yuki.
-Huh?
-Did you come to see Kaname?
Unfortunately, he doesn't
happen to be in right now.
-Um, it seems you
already know who I am.
-Hm.
You see, Yuki, I used
to live with Kaname.
And we drove over to
your place quite often.
I stayed inside the
car, but I always
watched you hugging
Kaname tightly.
OK, Yuki, you should
go home and go to bed.
You shouldn't walk around at
night, even here at the school.
YUKI: I know he
told me to go home,
but I'm already this close.
Just a peek.
And it's too cold outside
for me to wait for him there.
STUDENT: What is this?
There are 1,000
questions on this survey.
And Headmaster Cross
wants it filled out
by the end of the night?
How twisted is that guy?
STUDENT: Stop trying to answer
them like you actually care.
-A vampire who takes filling
out a survey seriously?
That's kind of weird.
-Why is a human child in here?
And she's staring.
Is she my fan?
-She's laughing at you.
Don't cause trouble
before school even starts.
I don't want my experience
here with Lord Kaname
to be ruined by some
foolish act of yours.
-She mentioned Kaname.
I guess that means
she likes him, too.
[clock ticking]
KANAME: So then.
I see you still don't know
the rules for the night class.
-I'm sorry.
I remember them now.
-Far too trusting.
-Yuki, you do
cruel things to me.
-Where-- where am I?
This-- this is Kaname's.
KANAME: Ruka.
[gasping]
RUKA: Lord Kaname!
I'm--
KANAME: Yes.
It's best to run away.
Yuki, you make me cruel.
-No!
That wasn't Kaname!
I'm scared!
There's so much blood!
WOMAN (VOICEOVER):
You know the truth.
CHILD (VOICEOVER): That
scary vampire will--
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): The
truth cannot be changed.
YUKI: Kaname wouldn't
do something like that.
This is just a bad dream!
-Listen, Yuki, when it
comes to taking human life,
they don't think twice about it.
They're beasts in human form.
Remember that.
And Kaname Kuran
is no different.
-Yeah, but Kaname
is the one who came
and saved my life that day.
Kaname is different
from the rest.
ZERO: So then, why are
you shaking, silly?
YUKI: It was that night
when my fears returned.
YUKI: I just wanted
to say thank you
for carrying me the other night.
YUKI: Kaname is so
different from me.
I finally understood that.
ZERO: Hey, are you asleep?
You'll catch a cold.
-Kaname?
-Let's go outside.
-Huh?
Kaname, are you-- Did
Kaname cover me up?
KANAME: I have
never told you why
it is that I pretend
to be unaware of what's
happening to you.
I realize how precarious the
peace is here at Cross Academy.
That's why I have given
a great deal of thought
to just who in this little
garden would best benefit Yuki.
I know that you would
never betray her
because you realize
you owe her that much.
And that is why I am
allowing you to live, Zero.
YUKI: Something inside
me changed that day,
but there is one thing
that will never change.
And that's the part of me
that will always love Kaname.
[music playing]