-So, you've decided.
-Maria, if you know
the way to save Zero,
then I want you to save him.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): If
this is the only way,
I'll offer myself in return.
-Come here, Yuki.
Good girl.
What is it?
-I just realized that for the
first time in my whole life,
I'm glad vampires find my
blood delicious 'cuz in return,
you will save Zero for me.
-It was me who drove
Zero to despair.
That is my real body.
It's easy to save Zero.
You see that boy, he only
needs to drink my blood.
[theme music]
-He needs to drink your blood?
-That's right, the blood
of his master, Shizuka Hio,
and then Zero cannot
fall to level E.
He will become a true
member of the night clan.
-Oh, sorry.
Rima, you're overdoing it.
-Akatsuki, come on,
why don't you join us?
-Sorry, I can't.
I have urgent
business to attend to.
-Really?
That's too bad.
-By the way, isn't it time
that we switch places.
-Um, but--
-Now, now, don't fuss.
-No fair.
We wanted to dance with Takuma.
-So do I.
-This isn't fair.
-Hey, no pushing.
-Are you all right?
You didn't sprain
your ankle, did you?
-No.
-Dorm vice-president, may
I have a minute, please?
Now you've attracted all
these girls around you,
I hope you're not planning
to eat them later.
-How rude.
I'm just being nice.
So what is this urgent business?
-I must first report to
the dorm president, Kuran.
-All right.
Hey, by the way, I don't see
that transfer student here
tonight.
Well, go on.
Take care of your
business matters.
I hope it's nothing
too troublesome.
-You alone?
-Where is President Kuran?
-I won't do it.
I won't dance with anyone
except Lord Kaname.
-Of course, you won't.
-Now, for your promise.
Offer your blood to me
for I am to be pitied.
I am being hunted, and because
of that I need more power.
-Pursued by the vampire hunters?
I understand why you
would want more power,
but if you then decide to
attack the other students
at the Academy, I will--
-Your blood alone is enough.
You do understand what it
means for a pureblood's fangs
to pierce you, don't you?
-Shizuka!
Let Yuki go.
-But, Zero, you--
Please, stay back, Zero.
I mean it.
-Move it, Yuki.
Why would you even--
-You don't understand.
She's the only one who
can save you, Zero.
-You think she can save me?
-Yes, she and I
already made a deal.
Listen, Zero, the only way
for you to control those urges
and for you to stop
becoming a level E
is for you to drink
this woman's blood.
Yes, I'm scared, but
I'm going to be fine.
So please, stay back.
-Even if what Yuki says
about your blood is true,
I can still beat you within
an inch of your life, Shizuka.
-Zero.
-Why are you trying to
stop me, she-- Yuki.
-This girl has tamed you.
Are you happy to have finally
heard your master's voice?
You cannot help
but obey me, Zero.
I'm back in my own body.
Now my voice has the
power to bind you.
-The power to bind him?
-This is convenient.
Keep holding Yuki.
You do understand, don't you?
I am the one responsible
for creating you
and that means I am your master.
You simply cannot
disobey me, Zero.
-Zero, let go.
You don't have to
force Zero to do this.
I will let you
drink my blood, OK?
-For four years now, this
body has been ravenous.
Did you truly believe that
your blood was enough?
-But you said that you
only needed my blood.
Please, stop.
You've tortured him enough.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you being
so cruel to him?
-I'm punishing him for
becoming so attached to you.
You're being cruel yourself.
Don't you know, Yuki,
that the choices you make
are causing Zero to suffer,
even I can see that.
-I thought if I was with
Zero things would be OK.
I wonder, Zero, if you could
ever forgive me someday.
Zero.
-You can't do it, Zero.
Just stay being my puppet
for now, all right?
You can't even squeeze those
fingers around my neck.
-Don't take anything
more away from me!
-Zero, no.
-But this is not
enough to kill me.
-I'll finish it right now.
I'll end it all.
-Zero.
-Those eyes say so much.
He doesn't even
need to think, he
knows in his heart he wants
to destroy himself with me.
-Zero.
-Shizuka, why are
you doing this?
Why are you playing with him?
I will not allow it.
I will not have you die.
-Don't interfere.
Zero and I have
unfinished business.
Besides, you have
no need to worry.
I have things well
under control,
and I have no intention
of dying here.
-Shizuka!
-Zero!
-Slow down.
Don't tell me you
plan to leave again?
-The only one who
left, Ichiru, was you.
-No, no.
What I meant was
the vampire blood.
-Zero.
Who's Ichiru?
-Aren't you going to
introduce us, Zero?
-He's my twin brother.
-Are you awake?
Look here, I brought you my
very own stamina packed gruel.
In vampire territory,
only vampires are allowed.
It's in Kaname's hands now.
He has control of
the night class.
Even I, the headmaster,
cannot interfere.
-It may be fine
as the headmaster,
but I want to know how the
hunter inside you feels.
-I'm going to leave
the food here for you.
-That's it, huh?
-This is what I can say.
Yuki, as well as Zero,
are not vampires.
-Oh, it's you.
-Will you stop?
Listen, we have no idea
what dorm president Kuran
is planning right now, so
until we do there's nothing--
-You're wrong!
Why?
Why doesn't he tell
us what he's planning?
I've told President Kuran that
I'll always be on his side,
that no matter what
happens I'm with him.
-Hanabusa.
-If you stop me, I
won't forgive you.
-Protect yourself, Zero.
I'm no longer the old me.
The one who followed you
around and slowed you down
is long gone.
You see, Zero, I
have been allowed
to drink Shizuka's blood.
The flesh and blood
of a pureblood
give you special
powers and abilities.
I know you crave it
too, just admit it.
-That's enough you two.
Will you just stop it?
No matter what happened
you two are brothers.
-If you get in the
way, I will kill you,
even if Shizuka
doesn't want me to.
-That's enough.
-I thought vampire
hunter guns are only
effective against vampires.
-I knew it.
-Zero.
-Stay back, Yuki.
-That's it, you're right, this
body is still human, Zero.
-Ichiru.
-Shizuka did let
me drink her blood,
but she-- she didn't
want my blood in return.
She never once
desired it at all.
-You're bleeding badly, Shizuka.
A vampire hunter's weapon can be
an incredibly dangerous thing.
Even a pureblood's extraordinary
healing power is restrained.
-Son of Kuran, why
did you come here?
-You see, this is the
first room that I ever
lived in at this academy.
-Oh, well, I really do like it.
There's no one
here to bother me.
-Yes.
-Let me rephrase
the question, why
did you choose to
come to this academy?
-To repay a debt.
It's also the perfect place
to assemble all my pieces.
You see, I think
you and I probably
have the same objective
in mind right now.
Shizuka, I'm just like you.
I will do anything for the
sake of the one I love.
-They wouldn't look at me.
Not dad, not mom, the
reason our master,
the only person who
looked at me, was you.
And then finally, I met her.
She's the one who saved me
from the depths of loneliness.
It was her crimson
petals in the darkness
that brought color into my life.
And still-- still it was you
who Shizuka chose and not me.
Why?
Why was it you, Zero?
But I've been by her
side this whole time,
but Shizuka still
doesn't look at me.
I've stayed closer to
her than anyone else.
-Even now, when she looks at
me, the only man Yuki truly
sees is-- well, you don't
seem surprised, Shizuka.
-No, you see, I intended
to take your life too.
I planned to use
Yuki as you assassin.
-She'd have been
the perfect choice.
-You foresaw this.
My healing powers
have been restrained
by the bullet in Zero's
gun, and you came here
to tear out my heart knowing it
would kill a pureblood like me.
I find it very strange
that in the end
this is the way things
have turned out.
The first time I met you,
when you were a little boy,
you desired the
same thing I did.
-That is one thing
that has not changed.
-I will make sure your
life was not in vain.
I promise to find the very
thing that you hated most,
and I will destroy
it once and for all,
those who twisted our fate,
the fate of the purebloods.
-You have drunk the blood
of another pureblood.
You have gained new powers,
but now an ominous future
is what awaits you.
Only jet black darkness lies
in your path now, Kaname.
-I'm well aware of that.
-This must mean--
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER): Lord
Kaname killed Shizuka Hio.
-The smell of blood is strong.
Shizuka?
-Ichiru.
Yuki, listen, you don't
know what's going on.
I have to kill Shizuka.
Let me go, Yuki.
-You haven't told me
what you're planning
to do after you've killed her.
What if-- what if what she
said is actually true, Zero?
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER): He
doesn't even need to think.
He knows in his heart he wants
to destroy himself with me.
-Is that really true?
When everything is finished, do
you want to end your life too?
-Yes.
You see, that's why
everything you've been doing
was unnecessary, Yuki.
-I only did it because I
didn't want you to die, Zero.
-Yuki, why?
Why do you insist on doing this?
You don't need to
care for me so much.
I'm really glad nothing
happened to you.
You stay here.
-Zero.
-It's true.
I did used to wish that I could
die along with that woman,
but that's not what I want now.
I'll be back, I promise.
It's true, Yuki.
No matter who is in your heart.
-No matter what, I'm still
going to stay by your side.
Listen, Zero, you have
to promise me something.
Promise me you'll keep
fighting so that I never
have to use this pistol.
-My promise to you is--
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I
believe in Zero, but--
-Disciplinary committee.
-Shizuka, what have they--
[theme music]