-[retches]
KANAME (VOICEOVER): The
time is getting closer now.
Very close.
[theme music]
GIRL 1: [giggles]
Are you all set?
GIRL 2: Of course.
They're homemade.
GIRL 3: Who are
you giving it to?
-Kaname.
[girls giggle]
-Everybody is so excited.
-That's because
they're all getting
ready for St.
Xocolatl's Day tomorrow.
-All the girls go around,
giving chocolates of the boys
they have crushes on to
proclaim their love for them.
I don't get it!
It's completely absurd!
Has everyone forgotten this is
a school of higher learning?
I am against it in every
way, shape, and form.
-You know, Class Rep, you
might get chocolates, too.
-[gasps]
-Would you please accept this?
-Huh?
Ruka?
Haah!
-Yeah, but we're not going
to get anything anyway.
-Yeah, it's all going to go
to those Night Class guys.
-Hey, Yori, are you giving
chocolates to anyone this year?
-Hm, no, not interested.
What about you?
-Uh, no, I don't think so.
-Hm, so then what's that?
-Aah!
Oh, this here?
This doesn't mean
anything. [chuckles]
-Then what's it for?
Uh.
-I maybe wrong.
But I believe someone
behind us is glaring at you.
-You're a member of the
Disciplinary Committee,
yet you're giving him that?
-Uh, no!
This would just be a token
of my appreciation to someone
I'm indebted to.
I haven't even decided if I'm
going to give it to him yet.
Let it go.
GIRL: What, Zero?
-Uh?
-[giggles]
-Oh, yeah!
I almost forgot.
We have Zero!
-Right, top of the
gray curve and a jock.
You're our only hope, Zero.
Get some for us, too!
Gaah, uh, uh.
[chuckles]
-It's probably
best if you don't.
-Yeah, good idea.
Never mind.
HEADMASTER: So then, tomorrow
is St. Xocolatl's Day.
The entire school is already
buzzing with excitement.
The truth about the
Night Class could easily
be revealed in all this frenzy.
I need you to be more
alert than usual.
Is that understood, Guardians?
-Yes, Headmaster.
-I don't see why you
don't just ban this event.
-Zero, if I were to do
that, there would be a riot.
This allows students to
let off a little steam.
Of course, the
Day Class is going
to fawn over the Night Class.
All of the vampires
are incredibly
accomplished and
beautiful people.
If they're our allies, then
they're a great resource to us.
-I think that look
means "how dare
you compliment them
in front of me?"
He's not happy.
-Yeah.
Got it.
I know all too
well that vampires
have been the enemies of
humans for many centuries.
But there are vampires out there
who want to peacefully coexist.
And I'm proud to educate the
children of such vampires.
Your generation can
build the bridge
that connects our two species.
Zero, look, I know
it's difficult.
But someday, you will come
to understand my philosophy.
-I doubt it.
Not unless you can make
the past disappear.
-They are nothing but
beasts in human form,
who drink the blood
from living humans.
That your view?
-Uh, yeah, I, uh, um,
Headma-- Father, here.
HEADMASTER: Ha?
-I have a St. Xocolatl's
Day gift for you.
And you, Zero, my
annual gift to you.
-It's 20 coupons for
Yuki's shoulder massages!
Yay!
-"A coupon good for one errand."
You've realized you've given
me the same gift every year
since grade school.
-Uh, oh, shut it!
Come on!
Lunch is about over.
-Oh, ho-ho, oh!
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
Why does he do that?
Why does the
headmaster have to say
things he knows will only
get Zero all worked up?
-I'd like you meet
to Zero Kiryu.
Be nice to him, Yuki.
His family was killed
by a bad vampire.
Help him get cleaned up.
I have some business with
the police I must attend to.
-So the bath is--
it's over here.
May I touch you?
Come on.
There is hot water
in the tub already.
Um, you want help
with your shirt?
Huh!
Can I clean that up?
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Every
time I did something,
I asked his permission.
But Zero never said a word.
Thank goodness, he's not hurt.
I approached Zero
cautiously because I
felt the boy in front of me
would fall to pieces otherwise.
[girls shrieking]
-Everyone seems
so excited today.
-Even though St.
Xocolatl's Day is tomorrow.
-I wonder how much
chocolate I'll get?
Akatsuki, so what do you say?
Shall we wager on
who will get more?
-You're pathetic.
-This is so annoying.
-I'm sure you'll get a
ton of chocolate, Shiki.
-Uh, Lord Kaname.
-Morning, Kaname.
-Shall we go?
[whistles]
-The exchange of
chocolates is prohibited
until the day of the event.
-I have to make sure
he gets my chocolates.
-You over there, no
climbing the walls!
-Huh?
Uh.
[shrieks]
[thud]
-Uh, huh?
-Thanks a lot.
-Nice, Zero!
-[gasps] I'm, I'm so sorry.
-If anyone breaks
the rules again,
this event may be
cancelled for good.
[cries of protest]
YUKI (VOICEOVER): You
don't have to say something
like that to make
the girls hate you.
[girls shrieking]
-Waah!
Ugh!
All right, no pushing.
Stand back!
-Good morning!
How is everyone today?
[girls cheer]
Hm, hm.
Play along, Akatsuki.
-I refuse.
-Good morning, Yuki.
-Oh, uh, good morning.
[girls grunt]
-Hello, Zero.
How are you feeling?
-[gasps]
-You take care.
-Listen, if you want to
challenge me, I'll be ready
and waiting anytime
you want, Kaname.
-Tch, that jerk.
-Hanabusa.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
Is Zero hiding something?
Does Kaname know something
about him that I don't?
Humph, I'm just reading
too much into things.
Hm-mm.
First, you chop it up. [hums]
I wonder if Kaname will be
happy that I gave him a gift.
Uh!
It doesn't matter.
It's just a token
of my appreciation.
My way of saying thank you.
That's all.
-[sighs]
YUKI: A token of
my appreciation.
Oh, eh, oh!
Aah!
[clattering]
-[gasping]
-Ignoring it and running away
won't change what's happening.
I don't know why you
insist on pushing yourself
to the limit like this.
-Shut up!
Uhh, ugh.
[gasping]
-It'll ease the pain.
Take it.
These attacks seem to be
occurring more frequently,
don't they?
I'm afraid things will only
get harder going forward.
There is no going
back with this.
I'm sorry.
But you do
understand, don't you?
[bell rings]
-[yawns]
-Tired again, huh?
-Yeah, just a little.
-You got back to the dorm much
later than usual last night.
Oh, I see.
You made chocolates.
-Well, that's what
I planned to do.
But I messed it up.
So I ended up
having to buy these.
-Oh, OK.
-And I'm such a loser when it
comes to this sort of thing.
-I don't know what
you were doing.
But we could hear
you all the way
from the boy's dorm last night.
-No, you didn't.
Shut up!
-Uh!
-Huh?
-Come on, hurry up before
the Guardians see us!
-I want to see Idol.
He's my favorite.
-Let's go.
Time for work.
-Um, hey, wait!
-Well, have a good one.
-Yeah, see you!
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I
don't know what it is,
but something's wrong
with Zero today.
He seems different.
[sighs]
Wait, he wouldn't be planning
something against Kaname,
would he?
No, what am I thinking?
Zero wouldn't go after
someone without a good reason.
That's not like him.
[girls shriek]
[whistling]
-Listen up!
No cutting in line.
-Wow!
This will be fun.
-This kind of thing
doesn't interest me.
-Just put up with it.
-OK, Day Class ladies,
it's almost that time.
Today's event is about to start.
Get ready to pass out as
many chocolates as you can.
And for you Night Class
gentlemen, stand by your gates
and accept the chocolates
as they're given to you.
We should approach today's event
with as much order as possible.
And listen, this is
not some kind of game.
These ladies take
this very seriously.
-Taking chocolates from
girls is my obligation!
-Wait!
It's not time yet, Aidou.
-Aidou.
AIDOU: Ungh?
-You must behave yourself today.
Is that understood?
-Eh, yes, of
course, Lord Kaname.
-Uh, thank you, Kaname.
I appreciate it.
Kaname is just amazing!
On the whistle, girls!
Ready?
[whistles]
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Hold on!
What are you doing, Shiki?
You must accept them as well.
-Hm?
-Sorry, everybody.
I'm bringing Shiki
to you right now.
-[groans]
GIRL: Kaname!
-Hm?
-Would you please accept this?
-Of course.
Thank you.
GIRL: It's nothing.
-Will you take mine, too?
-And mine?
-Thank you.
-I hope these girls
realize how fortunate they
are that Kaname is so nice.
-You look scary.
-The expression on your
face isn't any better.
They're giving you chocolates.
The least you could do is smile.
BOY: Um, Ruka?
-What is it?
-I got you this to
show you how I feel.
-Uhh.
-So tell me, what would
your blood type be?
-Huh?
It's-- it's type O.
[whistling]
-Idol!
I mean, Aido, stop!
I said all you can take are
their chocolates, nothing else!
-[sighs] All right then.
GIRLS: (IN UNISON)
Please accept this.
-I'm sorry, but
my hands are full.
I'm afraid I just
can't accept anymore.
-(IN UNISON) Oh no.
It's all right.
Please excuse us.
We're the ones who are sorry.
-Thanks for understanding.
Thank you, Yuki.
-Sure!
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Is
he leaving all ready?
-Don't get yourself hurt.
-Uh, I won't!
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I can't
believe I missed my chance.
-[groans]
Uh!
-Kaname!
It was on the ground.
YUKI: Zero!
-Glad to accept it.
Thank you, Yuki.
-Uh, yes, sure!
Ooh!
Why did you give it to
him without asking me?
You were so angry about it, too!
-I was watching you.
It got me so irritated.
Why didn't you hand
it to him yourself?
Ouch!
-I didn't know what to do.
I thought it might be
awkward if I gave him a gift.
-Why would you think that?
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Because
he's so different from me.
-[gasps]
[heartbeat]
YUKI (VOICEOVER): 10 years
ago, Kaname did something huge.
He saved my life.
But I don't know.
Maybe that was no
big deal to him.
To him, it must have
been a small incident.
-Lord Kaname.
Those must be a bother.
May I hold them?
-You can have them
all if you want.
This is the only one I want.
-All right!
Now, it's back to patrol, Zero!
Uh, Zero?
-[gasping]
Whoever's hiding
there, show yourself!
-Oh, um, it's just me.
I wanted to thank
you for yesterday.
So I made you this.
ZERO: Go away.
-Uh!
Um, but I--
-Just go!
-[gasps] Um, I'm so sorry.
-Aw, come on.
Don't look at me like that.
-Jeez, is Zero
playing hooky again?
-[hums]
-Where is everyone?
-Hm?
Oh, right.
No one else is here, are they?
I wonder where they went?
-[sighs]
Hello, Night Class.
What do you want?
-You know, you're a
little cocky, Zero Kiryu.
-You're just a human!
And the way you
treat Lord Kaname--
-We're really doing this?
-Yeah, but Takuma said
we should leave it alone.
-Look, he's right.
Hanabusa, Ruka, if
Lord Kaname finds out,
he'll tear you apart.
Zero, come on.
Just put that thing--
-(IN UNISON) So uncool.
-Shut up.
-Humph.
Interesting.
Come on then, vampires.
Go ahead.
I'm in a bad mood anyway.
-See?
It's that kind of
attitude that makes
people think you're cocky.
-Well, I did the best I could
to play the good guy here.
I'm not to blame
for what's next.
-Hold it right there!
Fighting is forbidden.
Didn't any of you read
the Student Handbook?
If you refuse to back down, then
as a member of the Disciplinary
Committee, you'll have
to come through me first.
-Now, that she's here--
-I'm over it.
-Yes, the mood is
completely ruined.
Let's go back to class.
-What are you doing, Zero?
This isn't like you.
Why would you do this?
Zero?
-Just leave me alone.
[retching]
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Zero.
It's like his heart
is impenetrable.
It's always been like this.
And maybe it always will be.
-Oh, found you.
What are you doing?
You're going to catch a cold.
You need to dry yourself
up a little better.
Here, you've got to
wear your top, too.
I guess this is something about
you that may never change.
You know, I wish you would
talk to me, even a little.
Oh, I almost forgot.
It's for you.
It's a chocolate.
And don't say it's like
grade school either.
This one's different.
This is the only one I
made that turned out right.
It's the only one of its
kind in the whole world!
So be grateful I'm
giving it to you.
Huh?
Why do you look like
you ate something awful?
Jeez!
-[gasps]
-Uh!
Zero?
-I said to leave me alone.
-Hm, uh?
"VLXXX V06 Epsilon."
What's a blood
tablet doing here?
-Well, it seems that
everyone is truly repentant.
But I have to say it was
pretty gutsy of Zero to take up
Aidou's challenge like he did.
Something must really
be eating at that boy.
-We can't help him.
Not now.
That occurrence four years
ago changed his life forever.
-[retches]
[coughing]
[music playing]