[footsteps]
ZERO (VOICEOVER): I
couldn't control myself.
I'm afraid this
will happen again.
And when it does, I'll end
up killing that person.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
I'll protect him.
I will be his ally.
-It's an ancient spell, a method
that the vampire hunters have
been using for a long time
to tame an unruly vampire.
The bracelet that I gave to
Yuki works in conjunction
with this crest.
-Uh!
[gasps]
Nyaah!
-[groans]
-Zero?
-He's perfectly fine.
You've simply immobilized
him for a bit.
Yuki, if Zero tries to
bite anyone ever again,
please use that
bracelet to stop him.
Kaname has agreed to let
Zero stay in the Day Class,
but only on that one condition.
-Kaname said that?
HEADMASTER: Since his dearest
Yuki made the request,
Kaname just couldn't say no.
I'm sorry.
I never wanted to use
this method on you at all.
Just try and make do with this.
And if you still crave
the taste of blood,
feel free to help yourself.
[thumping]
No!
[crash]
[groans]
-Uh, Zero!
Um.
-It's all right.
This is just fine.
[door closes]
HEADMASTER: [groans]
It's not all right.
[groans]
Make sure he stays
in line, Yuki.
If you don't, that man will--
-Oh, what man?
-Ugh.
[theme music]
[panting]
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Zero.
I guess he's skipping duty.
After what happened earlier,
I can't blame him if he is.
So Kaname did
grant me my request
to let Zero stay
in the Day Class.
HEADMASTER (VOICEOVER):
Since his dearest
Yuki made the request--
-Thank you, Kaname.
Hm.
-He bit someone I hold dear.
And I'm sorry, but
I just can't ignore
that you got bitten
by someone else.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I
will protect Zero.
That's what I decided.
[bell rings]
YUKI: Come on, Yori!
Hurry.
YORI: Yuki!
[both gasping]
-Safe!
Uh?
Did something happen?
-Didn't you hear, Yuki?
We're getting a new
Ethics lecturer today.
-Huh?
But why now?
-I don't know.
But I just saw him.
[girls swoon]
[class gasping]
-Seems word of my
arrival has preceded me.
The name is Toga Yagari.
And I will be your new teacher.
Nice to meet you.
-He's pretty cool for a teacher.
-Hm, yeah, I guess, but-- uh!
Zero.
-All right then, are
there any questions?
-Professor, are you single?
-I am.
-You have a girlfriend?
-You're fond of the personal
questions, aren't you?
-What do you do in
your spare time?
-You know how to fight?
-Have you ever kissed a girl?
-Do you believe in UFOs?
-Come on, let's have
some order here.
If you want to ask
this man a question,
raise your hand first!
You're up!
-That patch you're wearing, is
that some new fashion trend?
[gasping]
-Zero!
Um, sir, as a part of the
Disciplinary Committee,
I'll go bring him back.
-This was the cost I had to
pay to save someone's life.
-Zero, wait up!
Hey, come on, Zero!
Uh?
[sighs]
Being sent on an errand by
the headmaster has its perks,
doesn't it?
-Not really.
-Oh, hey, Zero, look!
Come over here!
YUKI (VOICEOVER): You know, this
feels like how it used to be.
I mean, Zero is still Zero,
even if he is a vampire now.
-I'm digging in!
ZERO: I wanted noodle soup.
-Hngh!
[sighs]
Yeah, but the sundaes
here are so good.
So Yori and I came here together
the other day, and-- hey, Zero,
by the way--
-Hm?
-That new teacher,
do you know him?
Uh, never mind.
You don't have to answer that.
It's just that he comes
across kind of scary.
-He's not.
When you get to know
him, he's actually--
-Excuse me.
But are you from the
Cross Academy Night Class.
You are, aren't you?
I knew it immediately.
You don't look like
everybody else does.
-Yeah, um, you see--
-Students from the elite class
aren't like everyone else.
-Hold on.
-There's someone named Aido
in the Night Class, right?
He likes sweets.
And he comes in here sometimes.
-I'm leaving.
-Uh.
-OK.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): I
smell like they do.
-Thanks for waiting, Zero.
Are-- uh.
Zero?
[panting]
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
Where did you go?
Zero!
Ugh!
Ugh.
Ow.
Oh no!
Uh!
-[growls]
[chuckles]
You know, your blood
smells delicious.
Let me drink every drop of it!
Aaargh!
-Don't just stand there, Yuki.
-Zero!
-It seems when I use
Artemis instead of you,
it doesn't like it.
-[snarls]
-Huh, so is that a Level E?
-[growls]
[sinister laughter]
YUKI: Takuma!
Senri!
-There we go.
-Why am I here?
You didn't need me.
-Uh, why are you two
outside doing this?
-If you want to know, stop by
the Moon Dormitory tonight.
-Huh?
-Then we'll discuss the reason
why we came for that Level E.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Maybe I really
didn't understand anything
about the long
tragic history that
binds humans and
vampires together.
MALE SPEAKER: I knew it.
-[gasps]
Zero!
You-- you can't stop me.
-No, I'll go, too.
-Huh?
-I borrowed this anti-vampire
gun from the headmaster.
-Why are you
bringing a gun here?
The Night Class students
are good people.
Put that away.
-You've got it wrong.
-Uh?
-If at any time I lose
the human part of me
and go out of control, use this.
-[gasps]
I could never do that.
Besides, if I need
to stop you, I
can always use the spell
the headmaster taught me.
-There will come a day when
that spell will not work on me.
You know this.
You saw that Level E today.
That is eventually
what I will become.
When it does, Yuki, I want
you to be the one to kill me.
-All right, I'll agree
to what you want.
But the reason is
because I don't
think that day is ever
going to come, Zero.
Humph, I just won't let it.
Zero, you have to
promise me something.
Promise me you'll keep
fighting so that I never
have to use this pistol.
-You two are awfully rough.
-Why are you here,
Hanabusa, Akatsuki?
-The vice president of our
dorm told us to escort you.
Now, you put that thing away.
It's dangerous.
-Welcome to the Moon Dormitory.
The two of us will
be your escorts.
Please, after you.
-Look at that.
They came.
-But what for?
-Put that away.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): The true
face of the vampire lives here.
AKATSUKI: This way.
-[gasps]
-Yuki and Zero, please
make yourselves at home.
I'm throwing a little party
tonight for my birthday.
Please enjoy yourselves.
YUKI: We came here on business.
I want to know more about
what happened today.
-Oh.
-I want to know
why you thought it
was OK to destroy
that Level E. I mean
he's a vampire,
just like you are!
-Actually, we are
not like them at all.
-Huh?
-Yuki, you must understand
that the Society of Vampires
is ruled entirely by a
few Purebloods and only
a handful of aristocrats.
Every student in the
Night Class is at least
an aristocrat or higher.
Below us are the
average vampires.
And in the ranks below
them are the vampires
who were once human.
-And then there
are those vampires
who don't even
make the rankings.
And they're known as Level E.
-Due to a number of
reasons, vampires
who began their lives as humans
will slowly lose their sanity,
falling into Level E. The
E standing for the "End."
Complete degeneration
and destruction.
We are no way
similar to vampires
who are originally human.
Please don't lump
us together again.
-Why do you have to
look down on them?
None of them wanted to become
a Level E in the first place.
It was your kind
that made them what--
-Exactly right.
And that's why it is our
duty to keep an eye on them
before they're so consumed
by their thirst for blood,
they'd grab any
human they can find.
MALE SPEAKER: They were
following my orders.
-Huh?
-I did it.
I'm the one who told Takuma and
Senri to hunt down the Level E
today.
-It was you, Kaname?
-Yuki, I'm surprised you would
come to such a dangerous place
simply because
Takuma asked you to.
-I wanted to find
out for myself.
-[sighs]
Did you now?
Come over here, Yuki, Zero.
Yuki, sit beside me.
-Huh?
-[sighs] It's all right.
-I'm fine here.
-Yuki.
-OK.
-[gasps]
-Beside me is the safest
place for you to be.
-You know, actually, I've been
meaning to thank you for the--
-To be honest, vampires
that were formerly humans
shouldn't really exist at all.
But centuries ago, in the
dark annals of history,
lies a time when the battle
between vampires and vampire
hunters was most violent.
Many humans were forcibly turned
into vampires at that time.
It was done to bolster
our numbers in battle.
Ever since that
wrong was committed,
it has been the duty
of the aristocrats
to oversee the vampires
who were once human.
And sometimes, that
duty means ending
their lives for
another's safety.
-It's the hunter's duty to
kill vampires, not yours.
KANAME: Then tell
me, why didn't you
kill that Level E when
you had the chance?
This must be your
injury from today.
Hold still.
I'll ease the pain.
-Huh?
[gasps]
Kaname.
KANAME: Perhaps, Zero,
you sympathize with him.
[group gasping]
-It's OK, Seiren.
It's my fault.
I said something that
I shouldn't have.
-How do you point a
gun at Lord Kaname?
Tearing you to shreds right
here wouldn't be enough!
However, I will restrain myself
while attending this academy.
I don't want to hinder the
headmaster's pacifist ideology.
But never forget, our
respect for one person
is what keeps us at this school.
And he's Lord
Kaname, a Pureblood.
-A Pureblood?
Is that true, Kaname?
YUKI (VOICEOVER): That's
the same kind of vampire
who attacked Zero
and his family.
-You look as if this
is the first time
you've heard this, Yuki.
Are you afraid?
-[gasps]
To tell you the truth,
I guess I've always
been a little bit afraid of you.
Even now, I'm still
a little bit afraid.
-Hey, don't forget, everyone,
this is my birthday party.
You've all got to celebrate.
Yuki and Zero are my
precious guests, too.
MALE SPEAKER: It's
been four years.
I never thought
he'd still be alive.
-The girl in the photograph
would be my lovely Yuki.
She's a very good girl.
Yuki and Zero keep an
eye on the Night Class.
-Did you hear?
A Level E wandered
into town today.
-So did you do your job?
-No.
Someone beat me to it.
-I wonder who it was-- the
hero who saved the town today.
-Don't play dumb.
I know for a fact that it was
done by a Night Class student.
They call it their duty, but
they simply enjoy hunting.
The only ones to hunt
vampires are vampire hunters
like myself.
-That may very well be.
But it is forbidden
for anyone to kill them
without good reason.
What's this all about?
What are you doing here anyway?
You're not the type to
blindly follow orders
from the Hunter Association.
-I made an oath.
-The solemn oath that was made
only between the two of us.
Ha-ha!
[microphone feedback]
Ow!
-[chuckles]
YUKI (VOICEOVER): It
doesn't hurt anymore.
Does Kaname really have
the power to do that?
He's just so different from me.
He's from a different world.
The air out here is--
-Shiki, you want to cut it?
-Sure.
Hold the key for me, Ichijo.
-You cut me.
-Sorry.
But don't waste it.
-Senri, you cut me on
purpose just now, didn't you?
-Uh!
Kaname, look, I'm--
I'm sorry, but I--
-Hm, hey, Yuki, won't
you dance with me?
-I-- I can't!
-[sighs]
-Is that all right,
letting her go like that?
KANAME: Eventually, Yuki
will come back to me.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I didn't
like that atmosphere.
Zero probably felt the same way.
-[gasping]
-It's so bland.
When compared to actual blood--
-Speaking of humans
turned vampire,
you heard of the
most dangerous kind?
-Huh?
-The rare one whose body
rejects the tablets.
-Huh?
-Zero!
-[gasping]
-Zero, are you all right?
Huh?
That's-- you can't take them?
You're not taking them?
Zer--
-I've tried to drink them.
I've tried so many times.
-Uh!
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
That means Zero has--
-[grunting]
-That hurts, Zero!
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
I have to stop him.
I have to.
I have to stop Zero!
-[gasps]
-Zero!
[gunshot]
MALE SPEAKER: I
never thought I'd
be killing my dear
student with this gun.
Curse me with your last
breath and die, vampire!
-Master.
[music playing]