-I thought you
were dead, Ichiru.
-So my big brother remembers me.
Don't look at me like that.
We were so close back
then, weren't we, Zero?
-However, If you're interested,
there is a way to save him.
Let's make a deal.
I want you to do something
that only you can do.
[theme music]
[knocking]
-You look awfully pale, Zero.
How unsightly.
They had such high
hopes for you back then.
Now, you can barely resist the
beast that lives within you.
In time, that beast will
completely control you.
Soon, you'll lose
all sense of self
and devolve completely
to a level E.
-Is that all you wanted to say?
-Not quite.
It's been years since
I've seen my other half.
I'd hoped that we'd
have a nice long chat.
Don't you want to
know about that night?
-Hey, she's oga--
If you don't leave,
you'll be captured by those
people from the hunter's
association.
-Maybe, you have known
this all along, Zero.
What had grown inside my
heart was a deep darkness.
-Zeto and Ichiru,
a weak body can
be fatal to a vampire hunter.
-You're right.
-Ultimately, Ichiru won't
be able to stay with Zero,
even though they are so close.
-Thank you for always
being nice to me.
It made me happy to the
point of hating you.
-Ichiru.
-I know you pitied me.
You still don't
understand, do you?
What it's like to be born a
twin, always being compared,
pitied.
You can't imagine
to know what it
feels like to know
you're not wanted.
Still, why that woman?
Huh, I wonder why.
-We meet again.
-What's the matter?
What are you crying for?
Did something sad happen?
-What about you?
Why are you crying?
-This is the room where Zero
suffered all by himself.
I have a chance to save Zero.
-It's all right, Yuki.
All that I ask is that
you just be yourself.
-Kaname.
-Well, you see, I
slowly began to realize
that our dear parents
had become people
I didn't care for at all.
And you, Zero, my favorite,
well, I've always hated you.
By the way, you should thank me.
I was the one who asked
Shizuka to keep you alive.
-So you could make
me suffer, and then
kill me by your own hand?
-Exactly.
Did you suffer having your
fate twisted by Shizuka?
Have you suffered as much as I?
Shizuka changed my fate too.
All the purebloods are
godlike in their powers.
-You think that woman's godlike?
-I'm afraid you
don't know anything
at all about Shizuka, Zero.
She made a promise
to me and kept it.
She promised to make
me healthy and she did.
I want to kill you,
but I might forgive you
if you come with me.
However, you must
agree to serve Shizuka.
-Sorry, no.
Not with somebody like you
who covets becoming a vampire.
Are you?
-You really don't
understand anything, Zero.
I see.
You're falling to level
E. I won't kill you.
I think I'll let
you suffer instead,
resent the corruption
coursing through you
and degenerate into
a senseless beast.
-Zero!
Ichiru.
-It's been quite a
long time, master.
-Zero.
Are you--
-Oh right, you're only
real student was Zero.
But I'm not the
same person I was.
Chances are that I could even
hold my own against you now.
-Ichiru, stop this.
-Why won't you fight?
-Regardless of what
you think, I always
considered you my student.
-Master.
Master.
-So dramatic.
-Ichiru!
-Zero.
What happened?
-Take care of my master.
-Zero, hold on.
Zero.
-So, what happened?
-It was nothing,
just an accident.
I ran into Ichiru.
-You mean, that wound is from--
-I think that anything
is possible now.
Tell me, do you still
intend to stay a bystander?
-Is it curfew already?
-Don't you know?
During the ball, curfews
are pretty much lifted.
Let's finish our work so
we can practice dancing.
This is our only
chance this year
to dance with the
night class students.
-I hope I get to
dance with Aido.
-I want Takuma.
You there, stop chattering
and get to work right now.
Yuki, would you stop
sitting around in a daze?
I don't what is wrong with you.
I mean, really,
it's because of you
that our class has to work
the ball in the first place.
Why?
From what I heard from when you
turned in your answer sheet,
all you'd written on
there was your name.
If I can't dance with Ruka,
it will be all your fault!
-Hey, isn't that blood?
-Was there a fight?
-What happened to Zero?
-Zero.
Hey, what's going on?
-You seen that transfer
student anywhere?
-Zero, you're bleeding.
What happened?
-It's nothing.
I'm all right now.
-OK, but you don't look
like you're all right, Zero.
You should just do what
you need to do, Zero.
Right here.
Go on.
Go ahead.
Just don't spill too much, OK?
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Zero
isn't hesitating like usual.
He's that desperate.
-Zero, what does my
blood taste like?
-Why do you want to know?
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Zero.
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER):
Let's make a deal.
If you want to save Zero
offer yourself to me,
or give me Kaname
Kuran's corpse as a gift.
-You are my faithful servant.
You can't kill me.
ICHIRU (VOICEOVER): Resent the
corruption coursing through you
and degenerate into
a senseless beast.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): !
Only calmed down after
I devoured Yuki's blood.
It's disgusting.
-Where are you going, Zero?
That's not the way
to the ballroom.
I wanted to have
a word with you.
I need you to really
be on your toes tonight
while guarding the ball, OK?
I'm serious.
That's an order from
me, the headmaster.
[knocking]
-Yuki, are you ready?
What?
You're going to wear
your uniform to the ball?
You know that even
as staff, we're
allowed to take turns dancing.
-Yes, but the headmaster has
reminded me of my duties.
He asked me to be extra
sharp on security tonight.
-What a mean father.
He doesn't want you to have fun?
-He's not mean, but--
-Here.
This is for you, Yuki.
-Who's it from?
It says it's from Kaname.
Kaname.
I can't believe--
-Zero, thank you so much
for working tonight.
-Seeing how you told
me it was an order,
I really didn't have much
of a choice, now did I?
-Oh my, Zero, you're
so scary, and I'd
say, as of late, you're
rather moody, too.
It's like you've
taken it upon yourself
to shoulder anything bad
that goes on around here.
It's not so much an order,
but more of a request really.
I want to protect our students
right to a peaceful campus
life.
And then, as for you, I want you
to enjoy the moment rather than
fear a future that
you cannot see.
What'd you think?
Did I sound cool now or what?
YUKI: Oh Zero.
-Huh?
-I didn't know you
were here already.
-Ah, my sweet Yuki
is all dressed up.
Please tell me you'll dance
with Daddy later, my daughter.
-All right, sure.
Later then, a short dance.
-Yah.
I'll come find you later.
-Let's go on in.
We're on duty and we
should take it seriously,
but we should also have fun too.
-Really?
I thought you told me you
weren't looking forward
to the ball.
-I wasn't.
Come on, let's get to work.
This looks good.
Seems like everything's under
control and running smoothly.
Come here, Zero.
A guy should wear his clothes
properly, at least for tonight.
What now?
No arguing, disciplinary
committee member.
Good.
And now, a rose in the
pocket for the men.
There.
You'd look so good
if you only smiled.
-I don't get it.
How can you keep on
smiling like that?
-Well, that's because
I-- because what I want
is for you to smile too, Zero.
-This way, please.
-Um, excuse me, Akatsuki,
I was looking for Kaname
but didn't see him.
Is he here?
-I believe the dorm president is
alone on the terrace right now.
-Great, thank you so much.
-What?
You didn't want me to tell her?
-It's fine.
-Ruka.
Ruka, I finished
up all the work I
had so I could attend the
ball and dance tonight.
Would you do me the
privilege of dancing with me?
-Do it to promote goodwill,
like the headmaster told us to.
-I won't dance with
some strange boy.
-Ruka.
-Kaname.
-Good evening, Yuki.
I'm happy you wore the dress.
-Yes, I just wanted to thank
you for giving me the dress.
Thank you very much.
-What's wrong, Yuki?
Why the strange
look on your face?
-Huh?
-Just a joke.
You're lovely.
That dress suits
you quite nicely.
Do me the honor of
dancing with me in return.
-Kaname, why aren't we dancing
in time to the music now?
-Because I wasn't
paying attention to it.
Let's dance slowly, shall we?
Like we did in the old days.
-I remember.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
Back then, I didn't
know if I'd ever be able
to dance with him again.
It was the time that I'd
just learned the waltz,
and I could only
dance it slowly.
-Yuki.
-This is cruel.
When will you stop
treating me like a child?
-That was never my intention.
-Oh, really?
The tell me why the
other night when
you put me to sleep, Kaname,
you erased all my memories
from that evening?
You took me away
from that place,
as if-- as if you
were trying to stop
a small child from
meddling in things.
-That's not it.
I don't think of you as a child.
I only wanted to protect you.
I thought that it was
the best thing to do.
-And where have you been?
-Have you seen that
transfer student?
-No, not yet.
I don't think she's here.
-Do you have a minute?
-Zero?
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER):
Yuki, let's make a deal.
If you want to save Zero,
kill Kaname Kuran for me.
Kaname Kuran only let's his
guard down in front of you.
It's something only you can do.
But, if you don't
want to do that--
KANAME (VOICEOVER): All that I
is that you just be yourself.
-I'm so sorry.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I have no idea
why she wants Kaname's life,
but my choice is made.
-Um, will you dance
with me, Zero?
-Wow, Shindo is so brave.
-I know, it's too bad Zero
always looks so scary.
He's pretty good-looking
if you take a closer look.
-After all, you
did rescue me once.
Or we-- we could just talk?
-I'm sorry, but I can't
dance and I'm busy.
Excuse me.
-Kaname, have you seen
Yuki around lately?
-I told you what your role is.
You are to be her shield.
It upsets me that
you've forgotten.
-What is is, Kaname?
You lost your temper?
What happened?
-I want someone to tie me down,
so I don't do anything rash.
-It's cold in here.
This must be the place.
-Hm, down here.
-Are you going to
believe me now, Akatsuki?
-Kuruizaki-hime, she was a Hio.
-You're right, she
did cast off her body.
-Why would she go
to all that trouble?
-You mustn't go any further.
-Why not?
What's going on?
Hey!
-Let's stop here, Hanabusa.
If Seiren here's and
telling us what to do,
then the dorm president
probably has some sort of plan.
Besides, there's
nothing the two of us
can do against a
pureblood anyway.
[theme music]