[FEMALE DJ] Welcome back,
we hope everyone's enjoying
this spectacular Sunday.
And speaking of spectacular,
there's a fireworks festival
going on
in Higashi-cho later today.
[FUTARO]
I've got a whole day to myself.
That means I can forget
the brats
and study to my heart's content!
[DJ continues indistinct]
Wait a second.
I should teach them
this formula here.
They could all solve
this problem,
even Yotsuba.
Ohh! One for Miku!
Uh...
What the hell am I doing?
Ugh! Why do I care
about that stuff?
-[doorbell rings]
-Huh?
Must be a loan shark.
Sorry, we can't pay it right...
now.
♪
[knocking on door]
[ITSUKI]
Don't shut the door on me!
Open up!
Hello?
I'll be quick.
I just have something for you.
My father left your pay,
so I came to drop it off.
[RAIHA] Stop shaking.
You're crumpling Yukichi's face!
You get five thousand yen
a day for each of us.
For two days,
that's fifty-thousand yen.
[RAIHA] Look, Mama,
he's not useless after all!
[FUTARO] At this rate,
we'll be debt-free in no time!
Well, that's all
I came here for.
[FUTARO]
I can't take this.
[RAIHA]
Huh?
It's true that I went there
twice with the intent
to tutor you girls.
But I didn't do anything.
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
You did make a move
on my sister.
Wait, you did what?
[FUTARO]
I thought we adjudicated that!
[ITSUKI] Either way,
you haven't done nothing.
Having you at our house,
It's beginning to change
something within the five of us.
-Five?
-[ITSUKI] Uhh!
Uh... No, I meant those four.
Anyway, I'm not going
to accept this money back,
so you might as well keep it and
do whatever you please with it.
[groaning]
Hey, Raiha. Is there anything
you've been wanting?
[beeping]
[coins clinking]
Aaah!
Hey, Big Brother! Check it out.
I won the big jackpot!
[laughs]
Yeah, that's cool!
Still don't see
why you're here, though.
Look, I didn't have a choice.
I know! You can take me
out to the arcade!
But I want you to come
with us, too, Itsuki.
Will you?
You could've said no!
No, I couldn't!
She's way too darn cute!
I know!
[FUTARO]
Bring it on!
[RAIHA]
Gotcha!
[BOTH giggling]
-[RAIHA] Whoa!
-[FUTARO] Ugh!
-[RAIHA] Over here.
-[FUTARO] It's rigged.
-[RAIHA giggling]
-[ITSUKI] Uh?
[laughing]
♪
Huh?
Raiha's really enjoying herself.
It's tough for her, you know,
because of our family's
debt situation.
I assume there's a whole list
of things she'd like to do.
That's why I want to make
all her wishes come true.
Ahhh!
Big Brother, Itsuki, look!
Can the three of us do that
before we go home?
♪
I don't know, that game
over there looks way better.
You said "all of her wishes."
Come on.
[FUTARO] On second thought,
I'll pass.
[RAIHA] Nice try, bro.
You ready, Itsuki?
[ITSUKI]
Uh, yeah.
Isn't this awesome?
It's just like a family photo!
-Is it?
[camera shutter clicks]
♪
What is going on
with your expression?
You look worse.
I love it!
Thanks a lot, both of you!
I'll cherish this thing forever!
♪
[RAIHA humming]
So much for spending
my precious Sunday on studying.
Well, I still have the evening.
You quintuplets had better
hit the books tonight too.
Eeh!
Wow, would you look at the time!
Okay, I'm suspicious!
I know you had homework.
Don't tell me
you haven't done it!
Go away! Stop following me!
Hey, Big Brother?
I see four Itsukis.
Huh? Uh!
Hey, look, it's Uesugi!
What's Itsuki doing
with that waste of space?
Ooh, were you two out
on a date? Our bad.
[ITSUKI]
Of course we're not!
Aww, hi!
You must be
Uesugi's little sister!
Uh-huh.
You know what?
You should come see
the fireworks with us!
Wow, really?
Wait a second.
I already made plans
to study today.
And you guys have homework!
[ALL gasp]
Pretty please?
Can we?
Well, of course we can.
But only...
-[whimpering]
-[FUTARO] ...after...
all of you...
are done with...
your work!
[cries]
We'll never finish in time
for the fireworks show!
[CROWD murmuring excitedly]
♪
[NINO] We made it!
[laughs]
[RAIHA]
Good work, everybody!
[YOTSUBA] When are the fireworks
supposed to start?
[ITSUKI]
They're from 7:00 to 8:00.
[ICHIKA] I'm gonna go
check out the stalls!
[FUTARO] What are they
so enthusiastic about?
Ooh! Wanna try
to catch a goldfish?
Sure!
-Yay!
♪
[FUTARO sighs]
Well, either way,
at least they actually did
their homework
for once in their lives.
They must've really wanted
to see the fireworks.
[ITSUKI]
Why the long face?
Lighten up, we're at a festival!
♪
Whoa!
Would you please stop
staring at me?
-[FUTARO] Oh, great.
-Huh?
The five of you are hard enough
to tell apart as it is.
Don't go changing
your hairstyle.
Ugh, I'm Itsuki!
And I'll do it the way I want!
It's on my head!
Come on now.
That just won't do.
When a girl changes her hair...
you should compliment her.
I know.
Wanna find out if girls really
do wear yukata with no undies?
That's not the norm anymore.
Don't bother.
Well, there's only one way
to be sure.
♪
Ichika, whoa!
I'm just messing with you.
-Ugh.
-Admit it.
I had you going there!
[cell phone buzzing]
Hey, why are you all
standing around wasting time?
Ichika, time to go.
Uh, sorry. Phone call! Yes.
Tonight, really?
Hmm?
[NINO]
And you!
It should've only been
the five of us.
So why are you tagging along?
Look, I just came here
for my little sister.
[RAIHA]
Big Brother!
Look what I got!
Yotsuba caught some fish for me!
♪
Don't you think
that many fish is overkill?
Well, I saw her looking up at me
with that adorable face
and I just couldn't resist!
And look at what else
she bought me!
[FUTARO] That's the last thing
we need today!
[RAIHA] Sorry, I couldn't wait
for the show.
Well, that was nice
of her, I guess.
Did you say thank you?
Thanks a lot, Yotsuba!
I love you!
Oh, my goodness, you are so
precious, you don't even know.
I wish you could be
my younger sister too!
Hang on, I just realized.
All I would have to do is get
hitched with Uesugi one day.
Then we really
would become sisters.
Do you have any idea
how stupid you sound right now?
And don't you get any ideas
about Yotsuba, mister!
I won't!
Sorry!
It's fine.
I'm back!
Well, shall we?
Hmm? Are you going somewhere?
Nino rented out the roof
of one of the shops for us.
The whole roof? Rich people!
Hold on, we can't go yet.
[ALL]
Huh?
[NINO] Did we really come
to a festival
and forget to buy
that one thing?
[ALL gasp]
[MIKU] She's right,
we haven't bought it.
[ICHIKA]
We almost forgot!
[ITSUKI] Do they have it
at one of the stalls?
[YOTSUBA]
Ooh, I can't wait to get it!
Do I want to know?
[QUINTUPLETS]
All together.
[overlapping chatter]
[FUTARO groans]
[QUINTUPLETS]
Let's go buy the thing!
For a set
of identical quintuplets,
you sure are different.
[CROWD chattering]
Stay close.
I don't want you
getting lost, okay?
Hold my sleeve.
[RAIHA]
'Kay!
Ugh, that salesman
was the worst!
Man, what a jerk.
[MAN] How about a freebie
for the pretty young lady?
So why didn't he give me any?
I look just like you!
Being quints is so complicated.
-Hey, Raiha!
-Huh?
You wanna go
and try out the ring toss?
Yeah, let's do it!
Don't go too far, okay?
Found the yakisoba!
Hey, put some spring
in your step!
What's the rush?
And why's she so peppy?
All of you are, actually.
What's the big deal
about the fireworks?
Well, it's just, our mom
really loved seeing them.
We've always watched the
fireworks together every year.
Even now that she's not here.
It's one of the most
important memories
we have of her.
♪
That's why we keep up
the tradition. It's special.
[FUTARO]
I understand that.
No wonder
she's so fixated on it.
[ANNOUNCER] Thank you for your
patience, ladies and gentlemen.
The fireworks display
is about to begin!
[CROWD cheering]
Come on, hurry!
Wait a sec.
[MAN]
Let's go!
[NINO]
Where is everyone?
Ow! Who stepped on my foot?
Yotsuba! Ichika!
Itsuki! Miku!
Here, grab on.
[NINO]
Why should I?
You won't make it like this.
Now, which way is it
to the spot you rented out?
Just so you know,
you aren't invited.
Yeah, you said that before.
You all need to watch together.
♪
[FUTARO]
This way?
[NINO] Yes, it's the roof
of that building.
[NINO/FUTARO panting]
[NINO]
I'm sure they're already here.
[firework whistling]
[explosions]
♪
Funny story.
I just realized.
I'm the only one who knows
which rooftop we're meeting on.
[fireworks continue]
[ticking]
[FUTARO] They say
Tokugawa Ieyasu was the first
to see fireworks in Japan.
They first started in China,
then spread to Europe,
then they made it
to Tanegashima.
[NINO]
This is so boring!
Why do I have to share
this great moment with you
and your stupid
fireworks trivia?
Hey, it was your own fault!
And none of them are answering
their cell phones, either.
I can't believe I finished
all that homework for nothing!
It just isn't fair!
[cell phone buzzing]
Hey, Yotsuba!
Where are you right now?
At the clock tower?
Right. Understood.
Stay there.
I'll come and get you.
Okay. Listen!
Your little sister
is totally fine.
-She's playing with Yotsuba.
-Cool.
Well, don't just stand there.
Start dialing!
All right.
Crap, I don't have
anybody's phone number!
How completely
useless can you be?
-[CROWD chattering]
-[FUTARO] Huh?
Hey. There's Ichika.
[NINO]
You're right, that's her!
[line beeping]
Not working.
Is the signal bad?
It's one of the most
important memories
that we have of her.
Stay right there.
I'll go find everyone.
It's better than being
stuck here alone with you.
Hmph!
That's for sure.
Don't let me down.
Make sure they get up here
in time, okay?
[CROWD oohing]
Ichika!
[panting]
Come with me.
Nino's waiting for you guys
on the rooftop.
Let's go.
Hey, punk. Get lost.
[FUTARO]
Who the heck is this guy?
What's your relationship
to Ichika?
My what?
I guess I'm her... friend?
Teacher? Colleague?
Not sure.
We're, uh...
acquaintances!
He's gone.
We're acquaintances!
♪
Is Ichika
in some kind of trouble?
[MIKU]
Futaro.
Ichik-- Oh, Miku.
Thank goodness.
I'm surprised you could find me.
You did make a scene.
[FUTARO]
True.
Uh... Come with me.
I have to stop Ichika.
-[MIKU] Wait up!
-Uh...
Um, I got stepped on.
You go ahead, Futaro.
Hop on my back.
♪
Okay. Can you see Ichika
from up there?
Ichika? I don't think so.
You can't run, though.
I'll slow you down.
This isn't working,
you're way too heavy.
♪
There, does that feel
any better?
Sure, I guess.
[FUTARO]
Huh? Is she mad at me?
Hey, Raiha, do you want me
to go buy you some takoyaki?
Ooh, and they've got yakisoba!
And okonomiyaki back there!
♪
Yotsuba. We have
to stay put, remember?
[stomach rumbling]
-Uh?
-[giggles]
[BOYS laughing]
Here. You can have this
to hold you over.
[chuckles awkwardly]
I owe you one.
[MIKU] So, did you say
you ran into Ichika?
[FUTARO]
Yeah.
She definitely knew I was there,
but then she took off
with some mustache dude.
Anybody you know?
Mm-mm.
I think I've seen her
getting out
of a mustache guy's car
before, though.
[FUTARO]
Seriously?
Okay, that sounds
really suspect.
Well, who cares?
Forty minutes left.
What's that girl up to?
At this rate,
the fireworks'll be done
before I round you guys up!
You're being nice,
and it doesn't involve studying.
I can't believe it.
Don't be rude.
I'm fully invested in this now.
Besides, I saw how hard
you worked to be here.
Think you can walk?
[MIKU]
Yeah.
Got a minute?
We're taking a survey of people
who came to see
the fireworks display.
What's the relationship
between you two?
What's your relationship
to Ichika?
Oops. There's no need
to ask that question.
You two are obviously a couple.
-[MIKU/FUTARO gasp]
-Duh.
[MIKU] Um, we're actually
not in a relationship.
[WOMAN 1] Really?
You sure look like you are.
♪
[MIKU/FUTARO gasp]
No, we're not.
It isn't what you think.
The two of us are just friends.
Yeah, acquaintances, at most!
Maybe "schoolmates"
is more fitting.
Mmm.
On second thought,
that doesn't quite cover it.
-She's more like my client...
-You know what, never mind.
We're so sorry
for bothering you.
-Futaro.
-Yeah?
Hmm?
Whoa.
What'd I do now?
Everything's fine. Never mind.
Futaro. Look.
Don't move, okay?
I'll go get her.
-Itsuki!
-Ah!
[groans]
Oh, great.
It's just you again.
At least try to conceal
your disappointment, please.
Miku's resting over there.
Let's meet up with her.
[ITSUKI]
Sure.
[FUTARO]] Good, now we're
just missing Ichika.
Can I ask you something?
How would you describe
our relationship?
That sure is a creepy question
just to ask me out of the blue.
Hmm. I would say you and I
are basically strangers.
Yeah, we're strangers at best.
Did you just say "at best"?
Besides,
you shouldn't need to ask.
If you think very hard
about this,
you should already know
the answer.
[fireworks exploding]
[CROWD oohing]
Anyway, we need to find Ichika.
Where could she have gone?
Hey, nice job.
I knew that you'd find
a way to track Itsuki down.
Ichi--
[ICHIKA]
This way.
The fireworks are great, huh?
[FUTARO]
Hey, what gives?
Aren't you gonna watch
with your sisters?
Stop freaking out and follow me!
Huh? Uesugi? Ugh!
[ICHIKA]
Do me a favor.
Don't tell the others
what happened earlier.
I'm sorry, but...
I can't watch the fireworks
with you this year.
[fireworks exploding]
♪
[BOTH]
Ahh!
♪
[ticking]
[QUINTUPLETS]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[FUTARO] I've calculated
the quintuplets'
collective bust size.
[ITSUKI]
What's with the robot?
[NINO]
It's 444 centimeters, right?
-[buzzer sounds]
-[FUTARO] 441.
[QUINTUPLETS]
441?
[ICHIKA]
That's enough math for today!