[groans]
What is wrong with this thing?
The sensors aren't working!
If the Fearsome Five
weren't bad enough,
now technology's failing me too?
Excuse me?
I'm here to tutor
for the Nakano family
on floor thirty.
My name is Uesugi.
I think
the door might be broken.
[door opens]
Hey!
[MIKU]
What are you doing out here?
Uh!
-Miku!
-Auto-locks.
These things are pretty much
everywhere these days.
Next time, put our apartment
number into this keypad.
It'll call us.
Uh, I mean, obviously.
I knew that.
[sighs]
[FUTARO] I made myself
look stupid right off the bat.
I have to recover, quickly!
-[MIKU] Well, shall we?
-Huh?
Uhh... Yeah, let's go.
You're here for a lesson.
Isn't that right?
[knocking on door]
Great, you just had to show up.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Uesugi! It's so good to see you!
Hey.
[groans]
Ehh!
I don't know...
It's gotta be here somewhere.
[YOTSUBA]
The white one, right?
Yeah, sorry.
You realize
it's after noon, don't you?
Is this thing
really yours, Ichika?
Whoa, so grown-up!
We have the same face.
It would look
just as good on you.
Wha...
You've had the same underwear
since grade school.
It's time to throw 'em out.
[screams]
Uesugi's here!
[shushing]
♪
But, I mean, does it look good?
Tell me the truth.
Do you think I--
Wear a trash bag for all I care,
just get downstairs.
Fine! It's not like
you'd know what's fashionable!
Well! We're all set up now!
Time for us to hit the books!
I think I'll sit out.
I'll just watch you guys.
Remember your promise.
Japanese history first.
And I'll just be studying
by myself, so don't mind me.
[FUTARO]
It's not ideal,
but compared
to where we started,
it's progress, at least.
[overlapping chatter]
[FUTARO]
I mean, they're human.
If I'm nice to them, we can
all reach an understanding.
I agree, Yotsuba.
There's no time
like the present, is there?
[NINO]
Come back for more?
I thought for sure you'd
given up on this pipe dream.
I hope you didn't come
all the way up here
just to take a nap again,
Sleeping Beauty.
[FUTARO] Says the person
who drugged me.
Oh, right, gotta be nice. Nice!
Yup, I'm back!
Why don't you join us, Nino!
Right, over my dead body.
[FUTARO] Guess four out
of five's not bad.
It's fine, she can have
a day off just this once.
-[YOTSUBA] Okay!
-[NINO] Oh, right, Yotsuba.
My friend who's on
the basketball team
was looking for somebody
to fill in for the next game.
You're the most athletic of us.
Why don't you go, right now?
Huh? Right now?
I don't know. I...
Well, she says that they've
only got five members,
and one just broke a bone.
If they don't find
a replacement soon,
they'll be disqualified.
It's really a shame.
[chuckles]
Hey, you're not... Hmm?
[NINO] And they've practiced
so hard, too.
I feel bad for them.
-Yotsuba.
-I'm really sorry, Uesugi!
But I can't abandon
someone in need!
Seriously?
Yeah, saying "no"
is kind of a weakness of hers.
By the way, Ichika,
didn't you mention
that you have to go
to work at two?
[ICHIKA]
Crap, I forgot!
-I'd better go!
-Huh?
And Itsuki.
Shouldn't you go
to a quieter spot,
like the library?
That's a good idea.
Well, uh...
Okay, everybody gather round.
It's time to start studying.
Futaro. Face it already.
Everybody's gone now.
[FUTARO] Damn that Nino,
always foiling my plans!
What's she trying to pull?
Oh! Miku, you're still here?
By the way, you owe me a juice,
since you drank mine.
[MIKU]
Yeah, I bought you one.
Ready to start the lesson?
Sure, let's go.
This is a matcha soda!
Miku, wait!
[MIKU]
Where shall we start?
[FUTARO]
How about the Kamakura period?
[NINO]
I'm sorry.
Since when have the two
of you been best buddies?
I know!
You have a soft spot for
boring-looking guys, don't you?
That was unnecessarily rude.
It's not all about good looks.
That was kind of rude too.
What? Are you trying to suggest
that I'm shallow?
Do you mean you only care
about inner beauty?
And what if I do?
[NINO]
Oh, of course.
That explains why
you don't mind being seen
in those shabby
old clothes of yours.
And those trashy nails
are fashionable?
Someone like you
would never understand.
I don't even want to.
That's enough, you two.
You're sisters,
so try to get along!
Does this really matter now?
I mean, you both
have studying to do!
Yeah, Nino.
Stop being a nuisance.
What did you call me?
[stomach rumbling]
If inner beauty's
so important to you,
then I say we make it
a little contest!
Let's find out which one
of us cooks better!
But how does that...
And if I win, then there's
no studying for today!
You're not going to take her up
on that, are you?
Futaro. You just sit down
and relax while I settle this.
Why don't you sit down?
[GIRLS panting]
Why is this happening to me?
Ta-da!
A Dutch baby with ham
and seasonal vegetables!
Omelet over rice.
[NINO]
All right!
Now, you get to decide
which one is better!
You don't have to eat mine.
It's okay, really!
Now, don't be silly.
You went to all the trouble
of making it!
Thanks, you two.
♪
Mmm.
[giggles]
♪
Huh.
Actually, these are
both delicious.
[BOTH]
Huh?
I think they're...
[muffled voice]
...just about equal.
Equal? Impossible!
[giggles]
You have no taste! I'm leaving!
What's with the attitude?
[water running]
[FUTARO]
We've lost most of the day.
Looks like Nino managed
to derail me once again.
I can't fall for it next time.
Sorry.
[FUTARO]
One thing's clear, though.
For some reason, Nino hates me
even more than
the other girls do.
Oh, well.
I guess I'll never reconcile
with her.
I think you can. Maybe.
Huh?
How, though?
If you face her in good faith,
she'll come around.
In good faith, huh?
But how do I do that?
[MIKU] What makes you think
I would know?
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
I mean, it's your job after all.
[FUTARO] Face her
in good faith. Okay.
Uhh! Uh-oh.
Oh, great.
[MIKU over intercom]
What?
Hey, I forgot my flashcards.
I'm taking a shower,
just come get them.
Uh, I don't know.
You sure that's okay?
Hey. I'm coming in.
[dryer whirring]
Miku! You're already out?
That's right, Miku's usually
pretty equanimous.
I'll just grab these and go.
[NINO]
Who's there? Miku?
I thought you wanted
to use the bathroom.
I'm done now.
[FUTARO]
Nino!
My contacts are
on the usual shelf.
Could you bring them over?
[FUTARO] She must be blind
without those things!
This is bad.
What's my next move?
So much for good faith.
I'm a dead man!
-Oh, crap.
-What's wrong?
Are you still mad at me because
of that conversation before?
[FUTARO]
Here she comes!
I gotta find
those contacts, and fast!
In here?
[NINO]
I know I took things too far.
♪
I feel bad about
what I did, okay?
♪
[FUTARO]
Where are you?
Not in there.
Look in the usual place.
It's the shelf right above that.
Huh? I could've sworn
they were here.
♪
[FUTARO groaning]
Face her in good faith?
I can't face her at all!
Abort!
I knew it, you are mad!
It's his fault. That stupid guy.
The only reason
he keeps coming to see us
is because
Papa ordered him to.
This house is for us sisters.
He doesn't belong here with us!
[FUTARO]
Where's all this coming from?
I've had enough!
I won't let him come back, ever!
Oww.
Nino! Watch out!
-[books clattering]
-[NINO screams]
[FUTARO] At that point,
I still hadn't realized it.
♪
Who... Who's there?
[whimpering]
♪
[ICHIKA]
Thanks so much for today, sir.
Don't mention it.
Great work as always, Ichika.
Till next time, okay?
Of course.
[FUTARO]
Together was one thing.
But one-on-one, these girls were
a different kind of terror.
[panting]
Thank you for filling in!
We're so lucky
to have you, Nakano.
[YOTSUBA]
Always happy to help!
Oh, yeah.
I was just about to ask you.
Would you like to join
the team officially?
♪
I was about to learn
a lesson, too.
That stuff Nino said earlier.
You have a soft spot for
boring-looking guys, don't you?
♪
It's not even true.
[FUTARO]] Maybe I was
the biggest idiot of them all.
-You, you intruder!
-No, I'm not!
I'm here because
I forgot to take--
Take what?
A naked picture?
You're a pervert!
That's so disgusting!
[FUTARO]
Let me finish my sentence!
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[BOTH gasp]
You're the worst.
Order in the court.
Your Honor.
Here's Exhibit A.
The defendant,
a part-time tutor,
lost control
of his primal urges,
offending an innocent
young woman
with his unspeakable lewdness.
Now, Uesugi.
As you are clearly featured
in this photograph,
how do you plead?
Um. Not guilty.
-Ha!
-Please, Your Honor.
You may speak, Plaintiff!
Let it be known,
the perpetrator gave
the impression he was leaving
and then waited for me
to exit the shower.
-Hey!
-Gotcha!
Huh? Wait! That's not what I--
And as punishment
for such a heinous crime,
I propose he be permanently
banned from this apartment!
[FUTARO] Don't you think
that's a little severe?
Sorry, but you should've
thought about that.
Come on. Please,
just hear me out, Ichika,
-I--
-Mmm.
-Your Honor?
-[chuckles]
[MIKU]
Objection.
Futaro may look like a criminal,
but he's not.
What? Eh, fine, I'll take it.
[MIKU]
I let him in by intercom.
Check the tapes.
This was all just an accident.
Miku!
I can't believe you're
actually taking this guy's side!
I mean, he admitted to it!
He came back in to take pics!
He just said "take."
You know, as in "get."
Your Honor,
Miku's only defending
this dirtbag
because she has a crush
on him. Hmph!
What? That's not true.
Miku. You believed in me.
I'm so happy!
Don't you come any closer.
-No fair!
-Ooh!
Are you too embarrassed to look
your boyfriend in the eye?
[MIKU] Now you're just
making things up.
Need I remind you
that this lowlife saw me naked?
It's not like there's
anything there to look at.
Maybe not for you,
but I have a figure!
We all look the same, genius!
[ITSUKI] Hey, now's not
the time to be arguing.
You stay out of it, Itsuki.
Yeah. And delete that photo
before I end your life!
[crying]
-Your Honor!
-Aw, there, there.
Let's see.
Even if Miku did let him in,
how did they end up like that?
My point exactly!
I knew you would
understand, Ichika!
The only explanation
is that this monster
threw himself at me!
No. I just told you--
Futaro. Did you touch her?
Well, yeah, but I was...
You know.
Your punishment is seppuku!
Whoa, that escalated quickly!
Okay, I need to do something!
Otherwise,
it's goodbye paycheck!
But how do I win them over?
The shelf--
[ITSUKI] Some books
fell off the shelves.
So he protected her?
♪
Makes sense
if you look carefully.
♪
So is that what happened?
That's it, precisely!
Thank you for your help, Itsuki!
I don't think I've done
anything for you to thank me.
I'm just trying to suggest
a possible explanation
for what happened.
-I see it.
-You're right.
Futaro's not ballsy enough
to commit a crime.
Hey, wait, but,
why are you throwing out
the case all of a sudden?
This trial isn't over yet!
Just let it go, Nino.
How dare you?
[ICHIKA]
Come on now, don't get so upset.
The five of us used to get along
really well, remember?
Either way, this all happened
because I was careless,
and I'm sorry.
[NINO]
We used to?
-Huh?
-[NINO] I...
Uh. Nino?
Uh...
[door opens, closes]
Should we try to talk
to her or what?
No. Just let her be
for now.
[FUTARO sighs]
Finally, I can
go home and study.
[cell phone chiming]
[RAIHA]
Hey, big bro, dinner's ready!
And get this,
we're having your favorite!
Curry udon!
[chuckles]
[FUTARO] Are they okay
with the way things are?
♪
Well, I guess
it's a family problem.
Hmm?
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Why are you so useless?
Huh?
She forgot her key,
but she doesn't want to ask
the other girls to let her back
inside for some reason.
What are you gawking at?
The last thing I want to see
right now is your dumb face.
Is that so?
I'm going home.
It's really none
of my business anyway.
Suit yourself.
[sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
Huh?
-[NINO] What's with you?
-Changed my mind.
There's a problem to solve.
And I don't feel like going home
until I figure it out.
I see. All you care about
is your stupid studying.
[FUTARO] Stupid studying?
That's a paradox.
Well, unless you mean
I study because I'm stupid.
Just shut up.
♪
Everyone's stupid,
that's why I hate them.
[FUTARO]
Everyone?
Your sisters, too?
-Nah, you're lying.
-[NINO] No, I'm not!
Anyone who'd let a creepy guy
like you into our house
is totally stupid.
They have to be! This house is--
"For us sisters, and he
doesn't belong here," right?
Uh.
[FUTARO]
That's what you said.
Leave me alone!
I don't think you're angry
just because you can't stand me.
Are you sure you hate them?
Because it seems like
it's the opposite.
You actually love
your sisters quite a bit.
And you consider me an outsider.
♪
[MIKU]
Save your breath.
Everything you just said
was way off the mark.
Don't assume
you understand me.
'Cause that'll never happen.
Creep.
You're still here?
But why?
Wait a second. I just...
Nino. I know how you must feel.
See, I have a sister too.
[NINO]
That's right!
I wasn't in the wrong!
-Huh?
-This is ridiculous.
What I am I sitting here
beating myself up for?
It's settled!
I've decided I won't accept you.
I don't care.
Even if it makes my sisters
hate me, it doesn't matter.
Nino. Come on.
Let's go back up.
It's getting late, okay?
-Miku?
-Uh?
Futaro's here too, huh?
That's perfect.
-Tomorrow, I--
-[NINO] Come on, Miku.
Let's get going.
[MIKU]
But, I wanted to--
I'm sure it's not
that important.
♪
[FUTARO]
It'll only get worse from here.
This is why I don't want
to get involved.
[ALL GIRLS]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[YOTSUBA]
Nino does the chores!
[NINO] We take turns
with the cooking, though.
-[YOTSUBA] 'Kay!
-[ITSUKI] How much water?
-[YOTSUBA] Just guess!
-[NINO] You're fired!
-[ITSUKI] Five rice bowls each!
-[ICHIKA] I ordered a pizza!
-[NINO] You're fired!
-[MIKU] Hey, I'm--
-[NINO] Fired!