♪
[ITSUKI] You never get up
this early, Ichika.
I'm kind of shocked.
Yeah, but I'm still the last one
to get out of bed.
Miku slept in my room, but I'm
not sure how early she got up.
Yotsuba went into town
to try and find her,
but she hasn't
come back yet either.
[panting]
Miku!
And what about him?
[ICHIKA] Who knows?
Maybe he's still asleep?
I can't believe
he really stayed the night.
Well. This'll be over soon
enough, so it's fine with me.
Huh?
You should sit in on
our studying sessions too, Nino.
They're actually
kind of a blast.
Nope, not interested.
Itsuki, don't let that creep
manipulate you!
Try being more honest
with yourself.
I don't know,
he's just a hard guy
for me to get along with.
We butted heads again
the other day.
I can't help it. I get hung up
on the smallest of things!
Sorry, Ichika, but I can't be
like you or Miku.
[gasps]
Actually, I think you can!
[ITSUKI]
Huh? What do you mean?
[ICHIKA giggles]
[ICHIKA] Let's part your hair
on the side like so.
There! Ta-da,
that's how you make a Miku!
Will you stop goofing around.
I'm being serious.
[laughs]
Aw, lighten up!
It's quintuplet humor!
No, Ichika!
Her hair's parted the wrong way!
And Itsuki, you need to make
your face look sleepier!
Let's get rid
of this cowlick too!
[ITSUKI] Cut it out, you two.
I'm not a doll!
You know, since Miku's out,
I say we try to pull
one over on Futaro!
Huh? You think so?
We'll need Miku's clothes, then.
[ITSUKI]
Uh, guys?
Oh, relax!
That idiot couldn't tell
a difference between us five
if his life depended on it.
[gasping]
What the hell
is going on?
There's a quint in the bed,
and I can't even tell
which one it is!
I slept in Miku's room
last night, right?
Yeah, and those look
like her PJs,
so this must be Miku.
Probably.
[grunts]
This is bad!
I can't be here
when she wakes up!
I'll just leave.
If anybody sees this, I am dead!
Huh? Miku?
But isn't she in her room?
So that must mean...
Those pajamas.
Uh, what's going on, Itsuki?
You can tell, huh?
Uh, look, about the midterms.
-[thuds]
-[gasping]
Okay. That's enough
conversation for now!
-I'm gonna go get dressed! Bye!
-[ITSUKI] Hey!
[grunts]
♪
[grunts softly]
Whatever, I'm done with this!
[door opens, closes]
[FUTARO]
Great job, me.
Now she'll definitely
be suspicious.
[sighs]
-[ICHIKA] Futaro!
-Huh?
You got any idea
where Miku might be?
Oh, uh, at the library?
[ICHIKA]
Good guess!
I know, let's study there today
for a change of pace!
[FUTARO]
Sure, sounds good!
[ICHIKA] Okay, I'll let
Yotsuba know, then.
♪
Uh-oh.
I still don't see Miku.
Guess she's not here.
[FUTARO]
Should I be doing this?
Even if I'm kicked
out of school.
I don't care.
You'll never be my tutor again!
[FUTARO] Just the thought
infuriates me. Forget her!
[ICHIKA] Some things are gonna
have to come from you.
So are you in?
[gasps]
[YOTSUBA]
Uesugi?
You look weird. Are you okay?
Uh, yeah. I'm fine.
Yotsuba, tell me something.
Let's say
that one of you failed
and she got held back a year
because of her bad grades.
What do you think you would do?
Mm? That's easy.
I'd redo my second year
with my sister.
Uh...
Well, then again, if only one
of us fails the midterm tests,
it'd probably be me.
[laughs]
But hey, with you here
to help us out,
I think we'll all be okay.
[chuckles]
-Uesugi?
-[ICHIKA] Futaro.
Sorry, but I think
I forgot my pencil case.
-Uh?
-It's fine.
You don't need it.
I got pens for days!
That's fine for right now,
but I'll want my stuff later.
We'll get started.
Could you grab it for me?
Sure.
[FUTARO panting]
♪
[MIKU grunts]
Miku, it's you!
Hey, Futaro.
I thought you went
to the library.
We forgot something.
You should head over there.
Your sisters
are waiting for you.
♪
Uh, wait a second!
Huh?
Well, uh...
About last night.
I just want to say.
Oh, last night?
Speaking of which, I meant
to ask you if you slept okay.
I couldn't get used
to the way your bed felt,
so I decided to sleep
on the living room floor
and now my back
is totally killing me!
♪
[sighs]
Oh. So you slept there.
Thank goodness.
[FUTARO] It's a lie, but it's
better for everybody this way.
Okay, I'm off to the library.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Now that that's done.
I've got one more lie
that remains to be told today.
Hey, wake up.
[moans softly]
[ITSUKI]
Oops! I'm sorry!
[gasps]
Oh.
It's you.
Ah, so this is where you were,
Miku.
What?
[ITSUKI gasps]
You were just avoiding me
to get out of studying!
-Well, nice try!
-But I...
-Grab your pen!
-Listen.
-Open your textbook!
-I'm not...
I'm done with being
Mr. Nice Guy!
One thing's for sure, you're not
gonna fail on my watch!
Wait a sec. I'm not--
Come to think of it, I wonder
where Itsuki could be right now?
She's probably busy
studying in her bedroom.
After all, I would be
hard-pressed to believe
that she's snoozing away at
her desk or something like that.
What's wrong, Miku?
[ICHIKA] Try being
more honest with yourself.
♪
Um...
Don't worry about me.
Nothing's wrong. Really.
♪
Then let's get started.
What are you working on now?
[ITSUKI]
Um, biology.
[FUTARO]
Okay, we'll keep going.
Is there anything
you don't understand?
[ITSUKI]
Well...
[FUTARO]
Oh, and, uh, real quick.
That fight we had.
Sorry about that.
♪
What fight do you mean?
Oops.
[laughs]
You wouldn't know,
would you, Miku?
For what it's worth,
I'm sorry, too.
Uh...
♪
Now you're the one
who's talking all weird, Miku!
Uh, never mind!
Anyway, about this one.
Oh, wow.
You already got that far?
I see.
Good job working on your own.
♪
Perfect scores!
On all of my midterms!
Whoa.
-[giggles]
-Same goes for us!
Not one mistake!
I hate to admit this, but
you're an exemplary educator.
-This can't be happening!
-[QUINTUPLETS] Yay!
-[FUTARO] I succeeded!
-Yay!
-This is great!
Almost like
some kind of dream! Uh...
Right.
Lower your expectations.
[groaning]
[ALL snoring softly]
All worn out.
They have worked hard.
Don't tell me you're staying
overnight to tutor us again?
The midterms are tomorrow.
We're going to use
all the time we've got left.
Do you hear this?
What's the big deal?
It's only for tonight.
[ALL]
Huh?
[FUTARO]
Today's the big day.
[ITSUKI moaning]
[ITSUKI]
Uesugi, you're up early.
[gasps]
Hey, Itsuki?
Silly question, but we're
supposed to report to school
by 8:30, correct?
Yup, 8:30.
And they said the exam'll start
15 minutes after that.
Huh.
Please tell me
that clock is broken.
[screams]
[QUINTUPLETS panting, groaning]
Pick up the pace, you slowpokes!
Hurry, Uesugi, or you're
gonna get left behind!
I thought you spoiled rich kids
had your own chauffeur!
Actually, Ebata is
our dad's personal secretary,
not a chauffeur!
Too bad he wasn't home
to give us a lift this morning!
Yeah. No kidding!
What happens
if we miss the test?
How would I ever explain that
to their father?
♪
I can't let people see me
without makeup on!
[FUTARO]
They've seen your sisters,
so what's the difference?
Thank you, dear.
[FUTARO] That's very noble
but poorly timed!
[snoring]
[FUTARO]
Stop sleeping!
I... can't... go on.
[panting]
Don't stop now!
No, it's all over for me.
[FUTARO]
Itsuki!
[panting]
I'm so hungry.
I need to eat something
right now!
[stomach rumbling]
Everything looks delicious!
We don't have time
to stand here and deliberate.
[ITSUKI] Which one of these
would you like?
Uh... I don't understand.
Let me buy you some breakfast.
I won't get into what for,
but I do feel like I owe you.
[FUTARO]
Everything looks delicious.
[ITSUKI]
I told you.
I'm sorry, I thought this was
a race against the clock!
[ALL panting and grunting]
Good. We're almost to school.
I know, but...
even if we make it in time,
do you honestly think
we can avoid failing?
Just so you're aware,
I'm going to tell my father
exactly what happens today.
Well, time wasn't on my side,
but I truly believe
I did everything I could.
So the rest is up to you.
♪
[ICHIKA] Come on, you two!
Clock's ticking!
[BOTH gasp, panting]
We're officially late.
The test is about to start.
[ITSUKI]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have stopped
for breakfast.
[MIKU]
It's my fault.
[ICHIKA] Wonder if
the guidance counselor
will cut us some slack.
-I know!
-[ALL] Huh?
[FUTARO] Itsuki, get Yotsuba
on the phone real quick.
Yotsuba. It's me.
You're at the school
already, right?
No, it's fine.
You just stay inside, okay?
Hey! Tell us what's going on!
[FUTARO]
I'm glad you asked.
It's called
Operation Doppelganger.
♪
Good morning, mister,
how's your day goin'?
-Hey, you! You're tardy!
-No, I'm not!
Remember this ribbon?
I was already here!
Hmm. That's true, I saw it
a few minutes ago.
Yeah, I had to step out.
A teacher asked me to help her.
Oh, I see.
Well, the bell's already rung.
Go and take your seat
for the exam.
Yes, sir!
♪
[sighs]
I move in the dark,
like a shadow.
Hmm?
♪
Oh, Mr. Guidance Counselor. Hi!
[GUIDANCE COUNSELOR]
Uh...
♪
So, how's the day
treatin' ya?
Uhh!
Uh. Good morning and all that!
Oh, yes, good morning.
That was odd.
I guess she's a busy kid.
I can't believe
I deceived a teacher.
What a disrespectful thing
to do!
Don't be such a goody-goody.
-[YOTSUBA] Uh!
-Huh?
Good, I found you guys!
I'm glad you made it!
It's the real one.
Hey, wait. Where's Uesugi?
♪
How's it goin' there, teach?
[GUIDANCE COUNSELOR grunts]
♪
You've sure got a lot
of nerve, don't you, boy?
Looks that way.
[GUIDANCE COUNSELOR]
You're going to the office!
♪
Futaro, no!
Go! Hurry!
You'll be all right without me!
Believe in yourselves
and the work you did!
[GUIDANCE COUNSELOR]
What are you blabbering about?
-'Kay!
-Let's ace this thing!
-It's gonna blow Futaro's mind!
-You pass too!
Hey, why are you
singling me out?
Time to give it all we've got!
[ITSUKI/ICHIKA/YOTSUBA/MIKU]
Let's do this! Yeah!
[NINO]
Yeah.
♪
So many tough questions.
But I'm good at history.
What if I scored
higher than Futaro?
Wonder what he'd say?
[groaning]
[gasps]
[YOTSUBA]
I remember!
If it's multiple choice
with five answers,
a lot of times
it's the fourth one.
[NINO]
A synonym for argument.
I'll come back to this.
"Debate" is a synonym
for "argument."
[NINO] I never asked you
for help, jerk.
[ICHIKA]
Done!
And I even have time left
for a nice nap!
♪
But maybe I'd better
look over my answers.
[ITSUKI]
I'm not going to let you leave!
♪
What are you talking about?
I told him that if any of you
fails an exam,
he'll have to step down
as your tutor.
This is for Raiha's sake!
No more, no less.
♪
[FUTARO] Come on, girls.
I'm counting on you.
♪
[FUTARO] I appreciate you
all gathering here today.
What's this about?
You're so formal!
You want to talk about
test results, don't you?
For all the ones we got wrong,
could you explain them?
Sure. But first things first,
I wanna see your scores.
No prob! I got a--
[ICHIKA]
I'd prefer not to.
[ALL gasp]
My grades are personal.
I refuse to show you.
[ICHIKA]
Itsuki?
[sighs]
Okay.
Well, the rest of you
can go ahead.
I'm ready.
Ta-da! Look!
I guess I got lucky in Japanese
'cause I ended up with a thirty!
I've never gotten grades
this good before!
I got a 68 in social studies,
and I just barely
failed everything else.
Could be worse.
The only decent result I got
was a 39 in math.
I think that's about the best
I can do for right now, though.
Listen, I may have failed
Japanese, math, science,
and social studies,
but for the record,
I did give it my best effort.
Unfortunately,
the only subject I managed
to not fail was science,
but at least I got
56 points on that.
-[YOTSUBA] Yay!
-[FUTARO] Damn it.
I know you're all bad at this,
but being reminded of it
is so depressing.
Oh, shut up.
Still, I'm not surprised each of
us passed a different subject,
since that's the way we tend
to be about everything.
-That's true!
-And besides,
compared to that time
we scored a hundred combined.
Yeah. You've definitely made
some good progress.
Miku.
Getting a 68 on a test
that hard is impressive,
even if your scores
were lopsided.
You should have confidence
in your history knowledge
and share it
with your sisters.
Yotsuba.
Some mistakes you make
are careless
and could be avoided.
Try to stay focused.
Understood, sir!
Ichika.
You'd score higher if you spent
more time on your answers.
Don't give up
until the very end.
Right.
Nino.
You refused to listen to me
until we were almost done.
Don't slack off just because
I won't be around.
Hmm.
Wait a second.
What do you mean,
you won't be around?
-I don't--
-Miku.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Itsuki. You've always been so...
stupidly awkward!
Say what?
You overthought
every single question,
so you didn't even
finish your exam!
That's something
I'm working on.
Well, as long
as you're aware of it.
Be careful from now on.
[cell phone ringing]
[gasps]
It's our dad.
Yes? It's Uesugi.
[FATHER] Ah, so you're
with Itsuki right now.
I was going
to ask them individually,
but let's hear it from you.
Sure.
[FATHER]
I'll know if you're lying.
I won't lie, but...
I do have a favor to ask.
I'd like you
to find your daughters
a more qualified tutor.
[FATHER]
Then am I to assume
the results were unsatisfactory?
Hello, Dad, it's me, Nino.
Could I ask you
a question, please?
Why'd you give him
an ultimatum like that?
As your father,
it's my responsibility
to make sure
you're taken care of.
I was testing this young man
to ensure
that he was suitable
for my girls.
[NINO] So you were acting
in our best interest?
Well, thanks for that.
But...
we won't be able to determine
if he's right for us
based on our
exam scores alone.
[FATHER] That's the
primary metric I've chosen.
All right. Fine.
Then I'll tell you!
We all avoided failing,
in all five of the subjects
that were on the midterm tests!
Uh!
[FATHER]
Is that true?
Would I lie to you?
Coming from you, Nino,
I'm inclined to believe it.
Uesugi will continue
instructing you.
Nino, did you just...
[NINO] None of us failed
in all five subjects,
which means it wasn't a lie.
[FUTARO]
Right, just misleading.
We were able to trick
our father this time,
but it probably
won't work again.
So you'd better get
to making it happen.
Okay, you got it.
Uh, Nino?
What the heck
was that all about?
Wait a minute, did I actually
pass all five subjects
and then forget somehow?
No way!
[NINO]
Keep dreaming!
[ITSUKI]
See, Miku? No need to worry.
It looks like we won't be rid
of this pain in the butt
for a little while longer.
Okay! Time to review!
Are you ready?
Yeah, I don't think so.
No running away.
Good thinking.
The most effective time
for studying
is after you receive
the results from a big exam.
But, it doesn't have
to be right after.
How about a reward?
You requested parfaits, right?
[QUINTUPLETS laughing]
[ICHIKA]
Futaro wants a parfait!
I know, that isn't
like him at all!
Okay, I'll have one. Jumbo size.
[FUTARO]
Is that a real thing?
All right, since you
each passed one subject,
you each get one serving.
Come on!
Cheapskate.
[FUTARO] I'll make it happen,
just wait and see.
Hey, Uesugi, we never saw
your midterm results!
-[paper rustling]
-[FUTARO grunting]
Hey! I didn't say
you could look at those!
[YOTSUBA]
What the... All hundreds?
[FUTARO]
Oh, man, I'm so embarrassed!
[ITSUKI] Are you trying to make
that your catchphrase or what?
[QUINTUPLETS]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[ICHIKA] What are
our best subjects? Math!
-[NINO] English.
-[MIKU] History.
-[YOTSUBA] Japanese!
-[ITSUKI] Science.
And together,
the five of us are...
[QUINTUPLETS]
The super No-fail Sisters!
[FUTARO] Would you stop
fantasizing and study?
[QUINTUPLETS]
No-Fail Sisters, go!