[fireworks exploding]
♪
[sighs]
It's pretty, huh?
Yeah!
♪
[MIKU]
What's taking him so long?
♪
Yeah, acquaintances, at most!
[ICHIKA]
When a girl changes her hair,
you should compliment her.
♪
[fireworks continue]
[ICHIKA] I got a work call
at the last minute.
Sorry. No fireworks for me.
♪
[chuckles]
But, hey, we're quints.
If they miss me, they can
just look at each other!
I don't think
that's how it works.
[ICHIKA] Gotta go,
my ride's waiting for me.
Not yet!
I need to know what's up!
-What for?
-Huh?
You sure care a lot.
What's that about?
Do you fuss over us
because you're our tutor?
[FUTARO]
Good question!
-[ICHIKA] Well?
-Uhh!
You've got a point!
To be honest with you,
even I don't understand
why I've been poking around
in your business so much!
Anyway, it was nice
talking to you.
Uhh...
Oh no! This is bad!
Someone from
my workplace is here!
Your work?
[ICHIKA] Yeah, I snuck away
without telling him anything.
[FUTARO]
Wait.
He was the one
with you before, right?
Oh crap, he's heading over here!
[FUTARO]
Whoa! Hey...
♪
[heart beating]
[FUTARO]
Uhh...
♪
Time for a break.
[FUTARO]
Right there, really?
Geez. How long are we
supposed to keep this up?
[ICHIKA]
Sorry, don't move yet.
If somebody saw us like this,
I wonder if they'd think
we were a couple.
[FUTARO]
Well, probably.
It's hard to read
the situation any other way.
Well, now I feel
a little guilty.
I mean, we're just friends.
♪
Wait a second.
Did you say friends?
Yeah, I don't know.
We can't say we're a couple
just because we hugged.
That's a little bit
over the top, right?
[FUTARO]
Oh, no, that's not what I meant!
At the end of the day,
I'm only a tutor.
If your father hadn't hired me,
we probably never would've
talked to each other.
So, it doesn't feel right
to call ourselves friends.
Do you even hear yourself?
Huh?
I seriously did consider
us two to be friends.
But if you don't feel
the same way,
then I guess it's not so.
It hurts, though.
No. I was...
Hang on.
-The two of us are just friends.
-Yeah, acquaintances, at most!
What about Miku?
Did I hurt her feelings?
-[MAN] Hello?
-Uh...
[MAN] Uh, yes!
I'm terribly sorry!
We've run into a bit of trouble.
Won't happen again!
Not during filming!
Filming?
Where do you work, anyway?
[ICHIKA] Well, he does work
in photography.
I understand.
[ICHIKA]
And I assist him with it.
You mean you're like his helper?
[ICHIKA]
Yeah.
I make the shots better.
Or I try to.
And it's my favorite thing
in the whole world to do.
♪
Do you have time
for that stuff, though?
If the five of you don't get
serious about academics,
there's no way you're going
to get into college.
[ICHIKA]
Tell me, Futaro.
What's the real reason
you study?
[FUTARO]
The real reason?
-Well, I--
-[MAN] Ichika!
There you are!
Hmm?
[MAN]
What are you doing over here?
Quick, we have to go!
Um, I don't know
what's happening,
but could you let go
of me, please?
Miku!
He must've gotten
the two of us mixed up!
[fireworks continue]
♪
[phone buzzing]
Itsuki, where are you right now?
[ITSUKI]
I don't know. I think I'm lost.
I probably won't get to you
before the fireworks are over.
Oh, don't be so ridiculous!
Don't worry. I'll make sure
you can see the...
I'm not giving up yet.
We are going to see
the fireworks display together!
♪
[FUTARO]
There. I see them!
Any luck?
I can't get through.
Nice going.
Why did you sneak out
of work like that?
♪
Not telling!
I mean, why should I?
According to you,
we're not even friends, anyway.
I know what I said, but...
Ugh, again,
why do I want to know?
It's not like I care what
this harebrained quintet does.
Not one bit!
What's your relationship
to Ichika?
Never mind.
Besides,
you shouldn't need to ask.
Hey, Futaro?
If you think very hard
about this,
you should already know
the answer.
-[fireworks continue]
-Uh?
[MIKU struggling]
You've got the wrong girl.
♪
[grunts]
You're the guy from before!
What are you trying
to pull here?
Who are you to her, anyway?
♪
Well, I'm...
I can't say
what we have is friendship,
but the word
I blurted out that day seems
like the most accurate
descriptor.
♪
The truth is, to Ichika.
To all of them.
I'm their partner,
and I want them back.
I don't know what that means,
but mind your own business!
If you looked at this one
a little closer,
you'd see she's not Ichika.
Hi there.
I could never mistake
somebody else for her!
Ichika's a talented
young actress,
and she's very important to me!
[FUTARO]
Huh?
Wait, this doesn't make sense.
How could there be
another Ichika?
[FUTARO]
Did you say "actress"?
So when you said you made
the shots look good.
Oh, wow.
Yotsuba, the fireworks show
is almost over.
-It'll be fine.
-Huh?
My four sisters and I may have
totally different preferences.
Like, when it comes
to food and stuff.
But no matter what,
we've always been one at heart.
That's why, I know that we'll be
able to find each other in time.
Yeah!
-[FUTARO] No way.
-[MAN] Ichika.
You're an actress?
You're a quintuplet?
-What?
Well, anyway!
We're already running late!
Let's go, Ichika.
Not so fast, buddy!
[MAN sighs]
1Listen, kid, I'm sorry
about the mix-up,
but what else
do you want from me?
Ichika's got
an important audition,
and she can't miss it.
Audition. But you can't!
The fireworks!
Tell the girls I'm sorry.
[MAN]
We should hurry.
Come on!
Hey, Futaro.
You should go with her.
[FUTARO]
What?
But I can't just
leave you here by yourself.
Don't worry.
I'm feeling a lot better now.
[FUTARO groans]
Now what?
-[YOTSUBA] Uh-oh!
-Hmm?
[YOTSUBA]
Looks like you're in a pickle!
[RAIHA]
Sure does!
It's you guys!
[FUTARO]
Ichika!
[ICHIKA gasps]
[panting]
[ICHIKA]
Futaro.
Where'd Mustache Man go?
He's going to pick up the car.
So you really are planning
to take off, then?
Yeah, but first,
I'll ask you again.
If you're just here to be
our part-time tutor,
why would you bother
to go out of your way for us?
Because we're partners.
It's a mutually beneficial
relationship.
[FUTARO]
Huh?
A script.
[ICHIKA] My boss scouted me
about six months ago.
Ever since then,
I've been playing
some minor roles
here and there.
I recently got the news that
there was a major part available
in this big-time movie.
Who knows? This film
could be my official debut.
And you're sure
you want to pursue this?
Yup! Hey, since you're here,
could you run
some lines with me?
You just read
for the male character.
-Ugh, why me?
-You said mutually beneficial.
[FUTARO]
I'll read it, no acting.
Great!
[giggles]
Here goes.
You ready?
[inhales deeply]
Yeah. Let's do it.
[clears throat]
Well, congrats
on your graduation.
Professor, thank you
for everything you've done.
The day you and I first met
in the classroom,
I have to admit that I...
I mean...
I'm just really happy
that I had you for a teacher.
And I'm lucky I got
to be your student.
♪
Oh, wow!
I knew my performance was good,
but I didn't expect you
to be that moved.
It's not that. I just didn't
think I'd ever hear you say
that you were glad
to have me as your teacher!
That was it?
Oh, I guess the car's here.
Well, see ya.
I'm getting that role.
Hope you guys have fun.
[FUTARO]
Hey.
[gasps]
Um?
I wish you would dispense
with the fake smile.
[chuckles nervously]
What?
Why are you always doing that?
Back in that alleyway,
when you were about to leave.
I know you put that face on
because you were hiding
your feelings.
It's infuriating.
I said you were my partner,
didn't I?
My family's in debt.
And I'm tutoring you girls
so that I can pay it off.
Of course, you've all been
giving me constant trouble.
In the end,
I was given a paycheck
despite the fact
that I hadn't succeeded.
If I'm getting paid,
then I at least want to earn it!
It's a matter of principle!
Now, you!
Answer my question.
You act cool.
So why were you trembling
back there?
When I started this new job
as an actress,
I thought I might finally
be able to stand tall
as the eldest sister.
I promised myself
I'd keep it a secret from them
until I actually
made it big.
That's why I didn't mention
to anybody else
that I had this audition.
And that's why I bailed
on the fireworks.
So if I bomb. Well...
I don't know
if I can face them.
The show's almost over now.
Oh, I gotta say,
I'm surprised you noticed such
a subtle change in my behavior
and knew something was up.
Talk about impressive.
Thank you.
It's nice to know that you think
I'm that perceptive.
[ICHIKA]
So you didn't notice.
I don't know you well enough
to pick up on those
miniscule details.
It's just,
I noticed that your smile
wasn't the same
as all the others.
Yeah, you got me.
So I can't even pretend
well enough to fool you?
That's kind of upsetting.
[FUTARO]
Maybe acting's not for you.
Whoa! Don't be so blunt!
Just so you know,
it would work out better for me
if you did blow it!
That way, there'd be nothing
to distract you from studying!
It's not a distraction!
This is the future
that I want to chase after!
[horn honking]
There you are!
Hurry up, let's go!
[ICHIKA]
Uh, yes sir!
Well, when you apologize
to them,
I'll be right there with you.
We're partners, after all.
[tires screeching]
Hello? Raiha?
Put Yotsuba on the phone please.
Well, Thank you all
for coming tonight.
I think we've seen everything
we need to see.
We'll be in touch soon.
-[door opens]
-Huh?
[BOTH panting]
I'm Ichika Nakano.
Sorry I'm late.
[MAN]
Mm-hmm.
[fireworks continue]
[cell phone buzzing]
Well, it took you long enough!
Where are you now?
Uh-huh? He said what?
♪
Hello? Yotsuba?
What? Are you kidding me?
Okay, are you ready to go?
Yes, thank you so much.
[MAN] Well, congrats
on your graduation.
Professor,
thank you for everything.
When you and I first met
in the classroom,
-I have to admit that I...
-I hope I'm smiling right.
How would my sisters do it
if they were here?
-Yotsuba would.
-[YOTSUBA giggles]
-[ICHIKA] And Miku.
-[MIKU laughs]
-[ICHIKA] Itsuki.
-[ITSUKI laughs]
-[ICHIKA] Then Nino.
-[NINO laughs]
♪
[ICHIKA]
I'm just really happy
that I had you for a teacher.
And I'm lucky I got
to be your student.
♪
[ALL gasp]
[WOMAN on PA system]
And that concludes
the fourteenth annual
Fall Fireworks Festival!
[snoring]
[ICHIKA] He's really sleeping
with his eyes open?
Creepy.
Ahh! Oh, hey!
Is the audition over?
Yeah. Thank you for coming.
Well now,
I never knew Ichika
was capable of all that.
Guess you must've done something
to inspire her.
Truthfully, I think I'm starting
to take interest in you, too.
Mwah! Huh?
Ichika? Where'd you go?
Where are we going?
The festival's closed.
To the park nearby.
They're all waiting
for you there.
They must be pretty angry.
You know, since I blew off
the fireworks show.
Maybe so. But hey.
Kinda early to give up, right?
♪
Oh! So you guys did make it!
Good to see ya!
It's not quite as good
as the real deal,
but you still get
to do it together.
Look, Uesugi,
we're all set to go!
We were just
too excited to wait!
Good thing you bought
those sparklers, huh?
Thank you.
Oh, and for babysitting.
[YOTSUBA]
Don't mention it! If anything,
Raiha was looking after me
most of the time.
And you!
I heard you wandered off
and left poor Itsuki
to fend for herself!
She was practically in tears!
[ITSUKI] Nino! I told you
not to tell him!
Uh, sorry.
I've waited all night
to give you a piece of my mind!
Good... job... to-day.
[FUTARO]
Don't hurt yourself.
Itsuki.
Hey. Why not come
over here and join us?
Miku, could you hand me some
from the bucket?
Uh-huh.
♪
Here.
[FUTARO]
Thanks.
You seem spaced out.
Okay, we're finally ready
to get started!
[ICHIKA]
You guys.
Sorry.
It's my fault
we messed up our tradition.
Please forgive me.
There's no reason
to beat yourself up.
Look, she really is sorry.
She should be!
Why didn't she keep us
in the know?
What happened was mostly
your fault, Ichika.
But then, I was the one
who didn't tell you all
where the place was, so...
Then there's me.
I'm embarrassed at how bad
my sense of direction can be.
And my foot.
That slowed things down
quite a bit, too.
I'm not too sure
what's going on here,
but I'm guessing at least part
of it is my fault somehow.
I kinda got distracted
by the food.
So you're...
Here. This is yours.
[giggles]
♪
[ITSUKI] Do you remember
what Mom used to tell us?
If one of us stumbles,
we'll overcome it together.
And if one of us
finds happiness,
then we should all share it.
[YOTSUBA]
Through joy.
[MIKU]
Sorrow.
[NINO]
Anger.
[ICHIKA]
And through love.
[ITSUKI] We're five-fifths,
and together, we are one!
[YOTSUBA gasps]
[ITSUKI laughs]
[MIKU giggles]
[ICHIKA giggles]
[NINO giggles]
[YOTSUBA laughs]
[QUINTUPLETS laughing
and shouting]
♪
[FUTARO]
Hmm? Hang on.
They're having a good time,
and Raiha's fast asleep.
That means I can
go home now, right?
It's late, but I could
still squeeze some studying in.
Ready?
[ALL laughing]
[FUTARO]
Not much of a finale.
[ALL laughing]
[FUTARO]
I guess I'll hang out for a bit.
[NINO]
We've got five more.
[ITSUKI] Okay,
let's all grab our favorite.
[QUINTUPLETS]
And go!
Aw, yeah!
Let's do it.
Same one, huh?
That doesn't happen much.
I'll just take the other one.
Seems like
you're pretty attached.
I'm their partner.
[YOTSUBA]
Miku!
These flashy ones
are more fun than the sparklers!
[MIKU]
No, I prefer this one.
[YOTSUBA]
Huh? That's the one you like?
Yeah. It is.
I haven't had a chance
to thank you yet.
You really helped me out there,
so I'll cooperate
with you more from now on.
We are partners, aren't we?
I should warn you though,
I'm not an easy study.
So be ready for that.
[snoring]
[chuckles awkwardly]
[ICHIKA]
Sheesh.
Good job today. And thank you.
Good night, Futaro.
[QUINTUPLETS]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[MIKU] Ichika's the most
popular one of us.
[YOTSUBA] Yeah, it's 'cause
of that whole "cool girl" vibe!
[ITSUKI]
That's not true!
I'm sure people like
you too, Yotsuba.
I mean, if I were ranking all
of us in order of popularity,
I'd say you're at least
in the top five!
[YOTSUBA]
Yay!