[ICHIKA] Miku,
what did you want to tell me?
[MIKU] Instead of equal,
we should be fair.
So, what's the fair thing to do?
[ICHIKA] Does this have to do
with the campfire dance?
[MIKU]
Um, yeah.
My classmates say
there's a legend.
That if you're holding hands
with someone
when the music stops,
it means you'll end up together.
I know!
Futaro has two hands, right?
So we can both
hold hands with him!
[ICHIKA coughs]
Sorry, what did you say?
Not important.
[ICHIKA] I guess I still have
a bad cough.
[MIKU]
You should be resting right now.
[ICHIKA] Aw, but I just changed
into my skiing clothes.
Who cares?
Go back to the cottage.
[FUTARO]
Oh, is that Ichika?
So your cold's
gotten worse, huh?
Guess we're in the same boat.
[ICHIKA] Wait. Did I ever
tell Futaro that I was sick?
What? Yeah,
you mentioned it when--
-Stop! I'll use speakerphone!
-[ICHIKA] Well, anyway,
if he's with you,
we'll talk later.
I'm kinda relieved, really.
I'm gonna head back after all.
Do me a favor.
Go find Itsuki
and keep her company.
I'm sure she's feeling lonely.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[FUTARO]
Weird.
I thought for sure
she'd be near the food.
That's not nice.
[FUTARO] Actually,
I don't think I've seen her
since we've been
out here skiing.
Huh.
She's not answering her phone.
I wonder if she went over
to try the advanced course.
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
What's wrong, Futaro?
You're sweating really badly.
Are you sick, or...
[FUTARO] I can't lie
to myself any longer.
I must've gotten it from Raiha.
So Ichika got it from me.
I feel so guilty.
You need to rest for a while.
A-ha! There you guys are!
-[MIKU screams]
-[YOTSUBA giggles]
[YOTSUBA] Did you really think
you would be safe from me here?
Yotsuba?
Right, I forgot.
I've caught
almost everybody now!
Only one left is Itsuki!
You can't find her either?
That's right! She stumped me!
[NINO]
Great.
Guess that makes
two people who can't be found.
Ichika, I thought I told you
to go back to bed.
Sorry, I tried!
Yotsuba caught me first!
Listen, you and Futaro
are both sick.
You have to go in
and lie down.
Yotsuba, did Itsuki
get away from you?
Well, no. I looked everywhere,
but there was no sign of her.
[MIKU]
What is it?
The situation could be
much more serious
than I originally thought.
Enough dramatics,
just tell us what's going on!
-[NINO] Lost?
-[FUTARO] Yeah.
We've been
all over this place, right?
One of us should've
seen her at some point.
I'm sure she's fine.
Well, what about her phone?
Ichika, are you sure
Itsuki said
that she was going out
on the slopes?
Uh, yeah.
[YOTSUBA] I don't think
I looked in that area yet!
We can't, Yotsuba.
All the teachers warned us
about that place.
The path hasn't been maintained,
so it's too dangerous
to go that way.
♪
I'll check in the cottage
one more time.
-[YOTSUBA] I'll get a teacher!
-Wait a second, guys.
We should look
a little longer first.
We can't waste time!
The best thing to do is
to get help now
in case she's injured!
But... I just feel like
Itsuki would rather not make
a mountain out of a molehill.
[FUTARO]
Huh?
Are you kidding me?
That's stupid!
Itsuki's life could be
on the line here!
We can't take this lightly!
♪
[ICHIKA]
Sorry.
[FUTARO]
Itsuki, where are you?
[breathing heavily, groans]
Futaro, you should
probably lie down.
-[YOTSUBA] Yeah, you're sick.
-[FUTARO] I can figure this out.
-I know I saw her today.
-[MIKU] Do you even hear me?
Hey there, Uesugi!
[ICHIKA] Did I ever tell Futaro
that I was sick?
-[NINO] Is that you, Kintaro?
-[ICHIKA] Uesugi!
[FUTARO] That's it!
I know what happened!
-Just forget it.
-[FUTARO] Wait a second.
I just had an idea.
So, tell us.
Do you know where to find her?
Don't worry.
Everything'll be fine.
Are you sure
I can depend on you?
Yeah.
-Ichika, you come with me.
-[ICHIKA gasps]
[ICHIKA] You want to search
from the ski lift?
I guess that is kinda smart.
Uh-huh. It's worth a try.
[ICHIKA] Not sure if we can
recognize her.
[gasps]
Um, actually, let's get off.
Hang on,
I think that might be her.
-Where?
-She's over there, you see?
The girl who's right
below our feet.
Oh. Um, well, I'm not so sure.
Maybe, or maybe not.
-I knew it.
-[gasps]
[FUTARO] I mean, the person
I pointed at is obviously a guy.
Found you.
You have terrible eyesight.
Without your glasses,
you're blind.
I'm sorry.
I took this kinda far.
You should've told us.
[ITSUKI]
How'd you know?
It took a while to figure
it out, but then I realized,
you called me "Uesugi"
when I fell down that slope.
Uesugi!
Ichika calls me
by my first name.
I get you mixed up,
but I have picked up
on a few things here and there.
[ICHIKA coughs]
That goofball.
I hope he managed
to track Itsuki down.
Are you sure Futaro's as bad
a guy as you make him out to be?
That's not what
I'm talking about!
But it's different
if we're talking relationships.
I mean, I don't really know
that much about him.
I think with men,
we need to be
way more selective than that.
[ICHIKA] Kinda sounds like
Itsuki's still going after him.
Don't worry.
Futaro isn't like our Dad, okay?
♪
Listen, I'm sorry.
I just needed
to make sure, so...
You are such an awkward person.
You just never
follow through. Huh.
Oh, gosh. Wait, Uesugi.
You're being too forward!
-Could you--
-[groans]
[shallow, rapid breathing]
[ITSUKI]
What's wrong?
Uesugi!
[WOMAN on speaker] The campfire
dance will begin shortly.
All students, please gather
in the common area.
I'm glad you brought him
back inside.
We'll let him rest
for a little while
and see if he feels better.
Would one of you please
bring over his belongings?
I will.
Ugh, this is all my fault.
-I'll watch him.
-But--
Yeah. I should stay here
with him too.
There's no point in you guys
hanging around.
Just let me sleep.
[NINO] Hey, you don't have
to be a jerk.
We're really worried
about you, here.
You heard him, girls.
Go on and have fun.
[NINO]
But...
This room will be off limits
for the remainder of the trip!
[ALL gasp]
Yes. You too.
[FUTARO]
Nino.
Can we talk for a sec?
Poor Futaro.
After all the reasons
he almost missed this trip,
he still made it.
Come on, we can't let it
end this way. Can we?
♪
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GIRL 1]
Who are you dancing with?
-[GIRL 2] Gosh, I don't know.
-[BOY 1] That's it.
I'm gonna ask her right now!
[BOY 2]
Hope she's not already taken.
Hey there.
Would you like to dance with me?
Wow.
This is stupid.
Nino, is there something wrong?
You seemed like
you were really excited
about dancing
with your soulmate.
Turns out he's not coming.
I saw Kintaro on the ski slopes.
He says he can't
make it tonight.
-I'm sorry.
-So it was him I ran into.
I wonder if he hates me
or something.
Well, uh...
Okay. I'll just hope
something changes.
Listen, Nino. Here's the thing--
[TEACHER 1]
Uesugi! What are you doing?
You should be in bed!
Cheer up. 'Kay?
♪
[NINO] Says the guy who's
the most beaten-down one of all.
He should worry
about himself for once!
[panting]
[NINO]
I can trust you, right?
Of course.
[NINO]
This is pointless.
[GIRLS chuckling]
Uh? Hey, where you going?
[NINO]
Ladies' room.
Hurry up, it's almost time
for the dance!
If you're not taken,
I guess I could dance with you.
Huh!
[MAEDA]
Really? Okay!
[gasps]
Drink this.
You're supposed to stay hydrated
when you're sick.
[ICHIKA]
Uh, okay, thanks.
Huh. I didn't know they made
a hot version of matcha soda.
Your fever's gone.
Well, that's good.
I'm kinda worried that I gave
my cold to Futaro, though.
[MIKU] Futaro's been
acting weird from the beginning.
[ICHIKA]
Hmm?
[MIKU]
Looking back on the trip so far,
I think he was probably sick
the whole time.
I wish I had paid
more attention.
I was just so preoccupied
with all of my own problems.
-Sorry, Miku.
-[MIKU] Huh?
[ICHIKA] I should've
turned him down for the dance.
If I'd put it together sooner,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
That whole legend thing
and your feelings.
And, of course,
my feelings, too.
♪
Huh? What's up?
[MIKU]
It's been bothering me.
I see the kind of relationship
you and Nino
and the others have with Futaro.
But mine is different.
I didn't think it would be fair
if I was special.
-Don't be silly.
-I know.
I'm done with that.
I want him for my own,
and I can't lie to myself
about feeling that way.
But for now,
I'll just leave it at this.
♪
The truth is, I like Futaro.
So I'm going to do what I want.
You should too.
All five of us should.
But I'm telling you now,
I'm gonna win.
♪
[chuckles]
Hmm. Man, this is disgusting.
You don't like it?
It's good for hydration,
I'll give you that.
Thanks anyway.
-Are you ready to go?
-Mm-hmm.
If I hadn't pretended
to be Ichika today...
Yotsuba? Did you get
all of Uesugi's stuff?
What's wrong?
See this?
It's his program book.
Look at all these notes.
He must've really been
excited for this.
And then I had to go
and drag him everywhere
even though he was sick.
I wrecked the whole thing.
I feel like such an idiot now.
Don't blame yourself.
He didn't tell us
how he was feeling.
It's not like
we can read his mind.
If we want to know
what he thinks,
we just have to ask him.
[gasps]
But hey, looks like his trip
wasn't a total loss.
[FUTARO]
Stories to tell Raiha.
Played the Quintuplet Game.
Test of courage prep
with Yotsuba.
Might go skiing
on the third day.
Yotsuba said
she would teach me how.
Lots to report!
Wow, that's a surprise!
Miku thinks the trip
turned out badly,
but it sounds like
he still had fun!
Who knows?
I'm gonna ask him straight-up!
You mean like right now?
Don't worry! I won't get caught!
Oh, Yotsuba.
I hope I can learn
how to be as straightforward
as she is someday.
[snoring]
Hey, um, head teacher?
Uh, yes! What's wrong?
The campfire dance
is wrapping up now.
Could you come
help me out, please?
Sure, lead the way.
[TEACHER 2]
Were you asleep?
[TEACHER 1]
What? Of course not!
[ITSUKI]
I tried to be bold like her,
but sneaking into his room
while the teacher was sleeping?
I think that was
a little too fearless!
Still, I can't leave him here
all alone, right?
I'd better turn on the lights.
Let's see.
I'm guessing the switch
is somewhere on this wall.
♪
[ALL]
Huh?
Whoa! You guys are in here too?
[ITSUKI]
Don't be so loud!
What on earth do you
all think you're doing here?
What about you, Nino?
I just came to drop off
my lucky charm
so that he could have
a speedy recovery!
I see. So we're all here because
we were worried about Futaro.
-Yeah.
-[giggles]
Aw, that's so nice!
We're quints. Of course
we had the same idea!
[NINO]
I told you, it wasn't like that!
[MIKU]
You're so stubborn.
♪
[ITSUKI]
Hey, Uesugi.
My sisters and I are hoping
you start feeling better
really soon.
I've been thinking,
and I realized I don't know much
about what kind
of person you are.
So when you wake up, tell me
more about yourself, okay?
I'll be waiting.
♪
[WOMAN on speakers] It's time
for the campfire finale!
[BOY]
All right, this is it!
[WOMAN on speakers] Please
join us for the countdown.
Ready?
[ALL]
Ten. Nine.
Eight. Seven.
Six. Five.
Four. Three.
Two. One.
Zero!
[ALL cheering, laughing]
♪
[RAIHA humming]
Ba-ba-ba-ba!
Ba-ba-ba-ba! Ba-ba-ba-ba!
-Ba-ba-ba-ba!
-[cell phone buzzing]
Ba ba-ba-ba...
Hey! Are you
at the venue right now?
Huh?
You what? How could you forget
something so important?
Fine. I'll bring it over, but...
Uh!
[grunts]
What's up? Was that Futaro?
Yeah, that idiot left
the ring here.
What kind of groom does that?
Like father, like son.
That's not something
to be proud of!
[laughing]
-Listen.
-Huh?
The guy I marry is gonna be way
smarter than you and Futaro!
Raiha! Please don't leave
Daddy all alone!
You're not dating yet, right?
Right?
[sighs]
As usual,
if it's not about work,
then my stupid brother
can't focus on it.
He's gotten better
since high school.
So at least
there's that, right?
[RAIHA]
Yeah, I know.
But I'm a little worried
that he'll turn out
to be a terrible husband.
Hang on. This is all
we have for breakfast?
Are the finances
really that bad?
[RAIHA]
That's not why.
There's no point in us
filling up right now.
We get to stuff our faces
later today, remember?
♪
[exclaims]
This place is like a castle.
♪
[WOMAN 1]
How could this have happened?
Huh?
I couldn't say.
It's a strange error.
[RAIHA] How many times
is she gonna change today?
I wonder if I'll ever get
to wear one of these.
[WOMAN 1]
Time to put up your hair.
Huh?
♪
[RAIHA exclaims]
A-ha! So there you are.
♪
[RAIHA groans]
Didn't anybody tell him
that this is
the most important day
of his life?
The least he could do
is not sleep through it.
I bet he would stay awake
if this was
an all-day math marathon.
Kinda makes me think
he doesn't even care...
That old thing.
I guess he held onto it.
That's sweet.
I hope you'll be
happy forever, big bro.
[bells tolling]
[PRIEST]
Introducing the groom.
[door opens]
[applause]
♪
-[MAEDA] Hey, punk.
-[WOMAN] Uesugi!
-'Sup?
-Best of luck!
No way! Don't pretend like
you don't know me!
You remember!
How could I forget?
Hey there, Maeda.
Good to see you both.
-[MAEDA] He hasn't changed.
-[WOMAN] Not at all.
Oh well. He's the guy
who brought us together,
so I'll always owe him one.
[WOMAN]
Right, the old campfire legend.
-Huh?
-Takes me back.
Me too.
Oh, and now that
I think about it,
it was the same
for these two.
[FUTARO] To be honest,
I don't remember much
about what happened.
But even though
the school trip was a disaster,
strangely enough,
I always look back on it fondly.
[PRIEST]
And now, the bride.
[FUTARO]
According to the legend,
when the annual campfire dance
reaches its finale,
whoever you're holding hands
with when the music stops
is destined to be with you
for the rest of your life.
♪
I think the reason I remember
those bittersweet moments
so happily...
is because they were there.
-[fireworks exploding]
-[STUDENTS chattering]
You were feeling this way
the whole time, huh?
I'm sorry
I didn't notice it before.
You're acting really out
of character, and I don't know
how to feel about it,
so please get back to normal!
The five of us are right here
beside you, okay, Futaro?
Don't worry. I'm using
my amazing healing power!
The school camp is over.
How do you feel
about your experience?
-[groans]
-[QUINTUPLETS gasp]
[YOTSUBA]
He's up!
[ITSUKI]
Do you feel any better?
-Wow, that charm really works!
-[NINO] Don't do that again.
[overlapping chatter
and laughter]
Be quiet.
[ALL]
Huh?
Give me some peace and quiet
so I can rest!
[ALL laughing]
[YOTSUBA]
Uesugi's real mad!
[ICHIKA]
Eh, he'll get over it.
You're too loud!
Go away!
[FUTARO]
I couldn't say it back then.
But I think
I can finally tell you.
Thank you for always being
by my side.
-[YOTSUBA] Uesugi!
-Futaro.
[FUTARO]
Hey, guys.
[overlapping chatter]
Let's go.
Are you feeling better
this morning?
Oh yeah. Now to make up for all
the time I lost in the hospital.
You can keep that for a while,
if you want.
-Sorry, did you say something?
-Not me.
Hey, Itsuki, do you have
to do that now?
I just get really hungry
in the mornings, okay?
I know! We should celebrate
Futaro's recovery!
How about we go
to the crepe shop--
Study! That's a great idea!
-[MIKU] Futaro.
-Hmm?
You're a big help.
Please stay a long time.
Studying again today?
Okay, let's do this!
Hold on.
I never agreed to study with--
Fine, I guess the rest of us can
get together without you, then.
Well, I mean, it's not like
I said no, either!
[ITSUKI]
Uesugi...
our success is in your hands.
That's right. And the finals
are coming up soon,
so I won't go easy on you!
-Oh, um, okay?
-Whoa, hey.
[FUTARO]
You better get ready!
-[NINO] Run!
-[screaming, laughing]
[FUTARO]
Come back here!
[YOTSUBA]
You sucker!