I'd like to thank everyone
for gathering here.
All we had to do
was come downstairs.
I kinda figured that
you would've given up by now.
Like I told you already,
we don't need
some know-it-all to tutor us.
If you're so smart,
then prove it to me.
-Prove it to you?
-[FUTARO] Shouldn't be hard.
You just have to take this test!
Here's your golden opportunity.
Pass the test, and I swear
I'll never speak to you again.
[ALL gasp]
What? Is he serious?
What test?
I don't even care, so why would
I take your dumb test?
All right, fine. I'll take it.
[NINO]
You can't be serious.
I just need to get
a passing grade.
And then I'll never have
to see your face again.
Aww, yeah! Let's do it!
Sounds pretty easy.
Define "passing grade."
Sixty-- no, wait.
I'd say a score of fifty
is adequate.
[sighs]
[NINO]
There's no reason we should have
to prove ourselves to you,
but it's time you learned
not to underestimate us.
[clock ticking]
[FUTARO]
Finished grading your tests!
Wow, you all scored
a hundred points!
[groans]
-Combined, that is.
-[YOTSUBA chuckles awkwardly]
[FUTARO]
This is abysmal.
[NINO] Run for it!
[panting]
[YOTSUBA giggles]
This is worse than I thought.
All five of these girls
could flunk out!
[panting]
Damn it.
I had no idea...
tutoring and doing
my own homework...
would be this difficult.
-Barely made it.
-[tires screeching]
What the...
That's one swanky limo.
Bet this is worth
at least a million.
Um, hi? What's your deal?
Stop staring and move aside.
-[YOTSUBA] Good morning, Futaro!
-You again?
-[ICHIKA] Oh hey, Futaro!
-[MIKU] Mmm.
Stop running! Get back here!
Hey, check it out!
I'm book free now!
Perfectly safe!
-We're not falling for that!
-Don't trust him.
He'll find a way
to teach us something.
Just what kind of person
do you think I am?
[ITSUKI] I'll admit that
each of us has shortcomings.
But we can manage just fine
without any help from you.
We don't need a chaperone
while we study.
What she said.
[FUTARO]
I see.
Then I can assume you reviewed
the test by yourselves.
[ALL chuckle awkwardly]
Question one:
Name the warlord
defeated by Mori Motonari
at the Battle of Itsukushima.
[ITSUKI chuckles]
No answer?
-It's no mystery.
-[GIRLS chattering]
[FUTARO]
These five girls abhor studying.
But... it seems they hate me
just as much.
I need to find a way to earn
their trust individually.
Huh? Wait a minute.
Miku answered
that question right.
So then, why...
Miku?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[WOMAN] One barbecue beef combo,
hold the-- Uh!
-[FUTARO] Hey, Miku.
-Hmm?
[chuckles awkwardly]
What you eatin' for lunch?
Um, let's see here,
you have a sandwich
for 350 yen, and, uh...
What kind of drink is that?
[MIKU]
Matcha Soda.
[FUTARO] Matcha?
Hmm, interesting.
I'm curious what
that flavor tastes like.
Well, I would let you
try some of mine,
but you're a mean person.
Can I at least
ask you something?
About that test question...
[YOTSUBA]
Hey, Mr. Tutor!
Ah! Yotsuba!
Sorry we all ran away
this morning.
It's nothing personal!
Eh, so, Miku--
Get a load of this!
My English homework!
I got every
single question wrong!
Come on. Let's give 'em
some privacy.
How come?
I was just gonna
ask him to help me.
You should, too.
Yeah.
That's a hard pass.
I mean, why bother?
We're all dumb.
[FUTARO]
All the more reason to study.
Studying sucks!
Do you really want to waste
your high school years
with your nose
stuck in a book?
We should be out there
enjoying our youth!
Falling in love!
[FUTARO]
Love.
There's no bigger waste of time
than ignoring scholastic
endeavors for romance.
Go ahead and fall in love
if you want.
You'll end up like
all the other fools in the world
who peak in high school
and do nothing else
with their lives.
That really struck a chord.
What's that about?
I'm not into anyone right now,
even if I wanted to date.
What about you, Miku?
Do you have a crush on anyone?
Ew. No way.
That was a weird reaction.
The look on her face.
As her sister, I know
what that look means!
No freaking way!
[BOTH together]
Miku is in love!
[FUTARO]
Huh?
Miku is in love?
I need to get these girls
studying one way or another.
Huh?
What the...
From Miku?
[MIKU] "Come to the rooftop
after school.
"There's something
I want to tell you.
I just can't hold it in
any longer."
[FUTARO]
Hold on!
A love letter?
Miku's in love with me?
But we just met three days ago!
Okay, what's that look
on your face about?
I swear, you're so creepy.
Hey! I am not creepy!
Miku's pranking me.
Be cool, you got this.
You don't need to put up
with this nonsense,
and you don't need
to go to the roof.
Nuh-uh!
You see?
I knew it was a juvenile prank
from the very beginning.
It's not like I secretly hoped
that she'd...
-[door opens]
-[gasps]
[squeaky voice]
...show up!
Thank goodness.
Hi. I'm glad you came.
I actually wanted to tell you
back in the cafeteria.
But I didn't want to risk
anybody hearing me.
[FUTARO]
What?
I don't like
where this is going.
Futaro. It's just...
[BOTH together]
Miku is in love!
[FUTARO]
Um, yeah?
[MIKU]
There's something...
-I need to tell you.
-[wind gusting]
I...
[FUTARO]
You?
[MIKU]
...I knew.
It was Sue Harukata.
Sue Harukata?
Right! I did it.
I'm good now.
Whoa! Timeout here!
You did what?
I don't understand
what you're trying to say.
The correct answer.
You don't remember it?
Your question.
My question?
Uh! That one?
Hey! Wait!
Why did you go through
so much trouble
to tell me that in private?
[MIKU gasps]
Ahh! I'm sorry!
Is that the Takeda crest?
Isn't that Takeda Shingen's?
You saw it?
Huh? Wha...
Uh. Yeah?
[whimpers]
-[MIKU cries]
-Huh?
Please.
Don't tell anyone
that I like
Sengoku period warlords.
Huh?
[MIKU]
It all started with a game
I borrowed from Yotsuba.
I became obsessed
with the ambitious warlords
and read a lot of books, too.
But the girls at school
are only into good-looking guys.
Actors, models,
you know, that type.
And I like hairy old men.
I'm weird.
[FUTARO]
Yeah, I can't unpack that.
But I'm not writing her off
as a student.
No way! There's still a chance.
♪
You're not weird.
You should be confident
about the things you like.
And, as it happens,
my last history test,
I landed a perfect score.
Wow, really?
Expect no less
from the top of the class!
Allow me to tutor you,
and I'll teach you things
about warlords you never knew!
Not a chance.
You think you know more
about them than I do?
All right, let's see
how you do on a pop quiz:
It's a commonly told story that
Nobunaga used to call
Hideyoshi a monkey,
but historians say
this is a false claim.
What was his actual nickname?
[FUTARO]
Whoa, that's a lot!
Okay, think.
What's Hideyoshi's nickname?
I'm pretty sure
my history teacher covered this.
♪
Was it "bald rat"?
That's correct.
I owe you one, Teach!
Do you know
about the theory that
Kenshin was actually a woman?
[FUTARO]
Yeah, totally. Old news.
And Mitsunari,
he didn't eat the persimmons.
[FUTARO]
Nope, not a bite.
Nobunaga served sake
in the skulls
of his vanquished enemies.
Uh, yeah. He sure did.
[chuckles]
I get it.
Warlords are the one thing
linking Miku and history.
She might not like studying,
but I can use this.
It's my way in!
Another one?
Nah. I should be
heading home, actually.
But I do want to talk
about this some more.
Shoot.
And I have so many stories
I bet you've never heard.
I know!
Let's make Japanese history
the focus
of our next tutoring session.
How's that?
Are you interested?
I mean, if you insist...
then okay.
[FUTARO]
Victory!
I need to locate
a decent study area.
The rest should be no problem.
My livelihood depends
on these girls.
-[vending machine rattles]
-I need to stay focused.
-[MIKU] Wait up.
-Yeah?
For you.
As a token of good will.
Here, try it.
You wanted to taste it earlier.
But don't worry.
This doesn't have
any of my snot in it.
No need to be scared.
[FUTARO]
Hold on,
did she really
just say, "snot"?
What's she talking about?
What's this? I stumped you?
You don't know about that one?
Bummer.
I thought you were
Mister "Top of the Class."
Turns out you're all talk.
I have nothing
to learn from you.
Farewell.
-[FUTARO grunts]
-[WOMAN screams]
[FUTARO]
I'm checking out these books.
Okay, sure.
[FUTARO] "All talk," am I?
How dare she?
I'm gonna tutor that smug brat
whether she likes it or not!
[horn blowing]
Miku! At long last,
you have arrived.
What do you want now, Futaro?
Use your wits to fight me!
Come again?
You're a Sengoku
trivia master, right?
Quiz me and I won't miss
a single question.
Not interested.
I'll just embarrass you.
Ha! Are you afraid I'll beat you
at your only skill?
[MIKU growls]
In Takeda Shingen's
"Furinkazan,"
which phrase refers to "wind."
I thought you'd
give me a hard one.
The answer is.
"As swift as the wind."
♪
Come on!
She's high-tailing it again?
You know what? I'm getting tired
of chasing after these girls!
They run from me,
they run from studying.
But she's not getting away!
♪
Whoa! Uesugi!
Uh, Yotsuba?
You should watch
where you're going
if you're gonna run around.
Do you know
if Miku came this way?
Yeah, I think I saw her
heading in that direction.
Thanks.
Man, where could she have gone?
Whoa! Uesugi!
[FUTARO]
Wait, how'd you get there?
You should watch
where you're going
if you're gonna run around.
[GIRLS] Left! Right! Left!
Right! Left!
What's wrong?
Sorry, Yotsuba.
Keep calm and listen close.
Your doppelganger
is standing over there.
[YOTSUBA] For real?
[gasps]
It's totally me!
That means you're dead.
Huh?
I don't wanna die!
Wow. I wonder what I should have
for my last meal?
Hey, is it just me,
or does she have longer hair?
And she took off her ribbon.
Where'd those headphones
come from?
-Hey, that's Miku!
-Oh, thank goodness!
[FUTARO] Think you can pull
a fast one on me, huh?
I'm sorry for lying
to you the other day!
I spent the past two days
reading every single book
in the library
about the Sengoku period!
That is such a lie!
[BOTH panting]
-I know, right?
-[laughing]
Uh, hmm?
-What the...
-Huh?
[FUTARO]
I put in the work studying!
I can talk to you
as an equal now!
[panting]
[MIKU]
Warlord shiritori.
Ryuzoji Takanobu.
Huh? [panting]
Oh! I know this game!
Fukushima Masanori.
From the battle in 1583,
he was the most prominent of
the Seven Spears of Shizugatake!
Kanamori Nagachika.
[MIKU]
Ka... Kawajiri Hidetaka.
Katakura Kojuro.
Uesugi Kagekatsu.
[FUTARO]
Tsu... Tsuda Nobuzumi.
Mi... Miyoshi Nagayoshi.
Shi... Shi... Shimazu Toyohisa.
Sa... Sanada Yukimura.
-I can't keep going.
-Ra... Ahh!
Why... are you trying...
so hard?
[bodies thud]
[BOTH panting]
[FUTARO]
You're pretty good at that.
I didn't think
you could keep up.
Yeah, well, the truth is,
I'm the slowest runner
in my class.
It's so hot.
Man. I need
a drink or something.
No shame.
She's just taking off
her clothes in public.
-Here.
-Eee!
Uh, sorry.
But you like this, don't you?
A hundred and ten yen
seems pretty steep to me,
but at least I know
there's no snot in it.
Ishida Mitsunari, right?
I learned about the anecdote
where he drank tea
with Otani Yoshitsugu's
snot in it.
You have no idea how many books
I read searching for that story.
But I couldn't find it.
Lucky for me,
Yotsuba happened to be there,
and I looked it up
on her phone.
Yotsuba?
Did you tell her
I like warlords?
I asked you not to.
No, I didn't tell her.
Why would you keep something
like that from your sisters?
[MIKU] Because they
wouldn't understand.
[FUTARO]
Why not?
They just wouldn't, okay?
I'm the biggest loser
of the five of us.
But you're actually doing
really well
compared to the rest of them!
You had the highest score
on that last exam.
You're just being nice.
Well, you shouldn't exactly be
proud of the grades you did get.
[MIKU]
I know.
We're not cut out for this.
My sisters can do
anything I can.
So if this is my best,
then it's also their best.
We are quintuplets!
[FUTARO]
Hang on.
If what Miku says is true,
then that means...
Just give up on me
and stop wasting your time.
[FUTARO] I was hired to tutor
all five of you.
Listen to me.
I'm not giving up on any of you.
I will make sure
you all graduate together
with smiles on your faces!
[chuckles]
It's a nice thought,
but it won't happen.
We're failures.
It took all five of us
to score a hundred.
Yeah. You're a bunch
of failures, all right.
Or so I believed, until today.
Just now, you said something
that gave me hope
for all of you.
You're quintuplets.
Your sisters can do anything
you can do, right?
Just flip that around.
Anything your sisters can do...
you can also do, Miku.
Take a look at this.
These are the test results.
See if you notice anything.
[MIKU]
Our scores are different.
None of us got
the same answers right!
[FUTARO]
Exactly.
Your average is 20 points,
so we have a lot of work ahead.
But I can see now
that you girls aren't hopeless.
Whatever one of you can do,
all of you can do.
Ichika...
Nino...
Yotsuba...
Itsuki.
And you, Miku.
I believe in you!
Each one of you has
the potential
to score one hundred.
All on your own!
♪
[MIKU]
That's a stretch.
-Sorry, but...
-[pops can]
...it won't work.
Don't put too much stock
in this quintuplets theory.
[FUTARO]
Ugh!
I wish the other four came too.
[groans]
I called to let them know
where we were.
Hold up!
You better rethink that number.
It's "the other three."
Miku's here!
[FUTARO]
Hey!
I'm so glad you decided to come!
We were just, uh...
[turning pages]
[chuckles]
[MIKU] Guess you could say
you got to me, Futaro.
I'm starting to think...
that maybe I can do
a little bit better, too.
So...
♪
...hope you're worth it.
I'm trusting you.
I'm your guy!
Miku, are you falling in love
with Uesugi or something?
♪
Ew, no way.
[FUTARO]
Huh?
[ALL]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[YOTSUBA] Who do you think
has the best grades
of the five of us? Miku!
[MIKU]
The brains of the quintuplets.
-The strategist.
-[YOTSUBA] What's a strategist?
[MIKU] A person who uses their
exceptional intellectual skills
to fine-tune and execute plans
of attack in Sengoku battles.
[YOTSUBA]
That's too many words!