-[YOTSUBA] Uesugi!
-Huh?
-What's up?
-Aah!
-[giggles]
-Whoa! Yotsuba!
Tomorrow's the big day!
-For what?
-Come on!
You know what day
I'm talking about!
See, look!
[giggles]
It's the school camping trip!
Have you read
the information booklet?
Can't say that I have.
They've got all kinds
of fun activities!
Outdoor cooking and skiing,
fishing, hiking, of course.
And then, there's the campfire!
Where the dance happens!
Rumor is, whoever's paired up
when the music stops
will be destined to spend the
rest of their lives together!
I heard that a lot of people
have ended up dating
because of it,
so the legend's gotta be legit!
Like I said,
students shouldn't date.
It's just a waste of your time.
Aw. That's sad!
If you had feelings
for somebody,
you would want to go out
with them, right?
Wouldn't you, Miku?
-Miku?
-Hmm?
Wait, why do we date people
we like, anyway?
-Huh?
[ICHIKA]
That's easy.
When you like somebody,
you want nothing more
than to be with them.
Miku should know
that feeling pretty well.
No. I don't.
All right.
Enough foolishness.
It's time to start studying!
Again? I'm not ready!
I have a shoot,
so I'll have to skip out.
Sorry. I sent you
a text earlier.
Huh?
Yeah, and I'd better
get set for tomorrow.
-[giggling]
-Hey, you can't just take off!
-Should have known.
-[ICHIKA] Miku.
My class has a meeting
about the camping trip later on.
Do the usual, please?
[MIKU]
Okay.
♪
[FUTARO]
The usual?
What kind of shady operation
are they up to?
Ichika? But I thought
she just left for work.
[gasps]
It can't be!
Is that Miku?
It's uncanny!
Oh, good.
You made it.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
[MIKU]
Sure.
You're Maeda, right?
Where is everybody?
Um...
Actually, there's no meeting.
I lied to you.
What?
Look. If you'll have me,
I'd really like to dance
with you at the campfire.
[MIKU]
With me? Why?
Uh, well, you know.
I... I really like you.
[MIKU]
Didn't expect that.
But Ichika's cute, so she
probably gets this all the time.
Thanks for that. I'll get back
to you later, okay? Bye.
I need an answer now.
Don't leave me hanging, Nakano.
[FUTARO] If you lie,
it comes back to haunt you.
-[MIKU] Um...
-[FUTARO] Oh well,
you reap what you sow.
[MAEDA]
Hang on.
Something's a little different
about you today.
-I think it's your hair.
-Really?
You're a quintuplet,
right, Nakano?
You and your sisters
all look alike.
You tryin' to pull
a fast one on me?
There you are. I've been
looking for you, Ichika.
Your sisters want
to talk to you.
You should go find them.
Futaro, I...
Now listen here, buddy,
this is between me
and Nakano, not you.
And I don't know what makes
you think you can call her
by her first name
like that, but don't!
Give her some time
to consider!
Think about someone
else's feelings for once!
[MIKU] That's not very
convincing coming from him.
This is none of your
frickin' business!
Quit being nosy and leave!
Actually, it is my business.
-Stop it.
-Oh yeah?
That's it.
[MIKU]
Please calm down!
[MAEDA]
Get lost, punk!
Sorry. I promised Futaro
I would dance with him!
-Huh?
-Hold on. I mean--
-Yeah, right!
That's a lie. You're way
out of this nerd's league!
No! That isn't true at all!
Futaro is, uh, um...
really cool.
[MAEDA]
What? Are you guys dating?
Yeah! We're such lovebirds!
Come on,
let's walk home together!
Uh, sure.
We'll go with that.
Hold it!
If you really are a couple,
shouldn't you at least
hold each other's hands?
What's wrong?
You can't do it?
That's kinda suspicious.
No, it's not.
It's not like every couple
does things
exactly the same wa--
Mi-- Ichika!
Um, listen.
I'm not blushing 'cause I'm
holding hands with my boyfriend.
You know, because we totally
do this all the time.
Damn it!
All right, fine, I believe you.
Maeda? This is probably
a bad time to ask,
but what made you want to
confess something so personal?
You're really twisting
the knife.
[MIKU]
Sorry.
Um, well, I guess,
you do it because you want
that person all to yourself.
Or somethin'.
[MIKU]
Oh.
You want them all to yourself.
Ugh. What the hell am I sayin'?
Look! Don't you give
Nakano trouble!
Trust me, most of the time,
it's Nakano giving me
the trouble.
Aw, you're so silly!
Let's head home, Futaro.
[whispers] You don't have
to cling so tight.
This is what Ichika would do.
That means I have to do it.
Don't worry, it's fine.
Anyway, you said no.
You sure that was okay?
Of course. Ichika's putting
work first right now.
I know, but what about
the whole campfire dance thing?
[YOTSUBA]
Hey, there you guys are!
Well, clock's ticking!
Huh?
[YOTSUBA] We're going
to pick out some new outfits
for you to wear
on the camping trip!
Here's what I picked out.
It's loud with lots of color!
I honestly can't tell
whether you're messing with me.
Traditional style.
That's what suits you best.
Don't you think
this is too traditional?
I decided I would
pick something
that makes you look
a bit manlier.
And this is your idea
of manliness?
Nino's thinking hard!
She's focused!
Why are none of you
taking this seriously?
Um, are you sure?
The cost.
We didn't buy that
for your sake.
We just couldn't be seen
in public with you
looking like a hobo.
You know, the way we're going
out on the town with you
and helping you pick out
all these new outfits and stuff,
it's almost like
we're on a date, huh?
This is just
a normal shopping trip.
It's a waste of time
for high schoolers to date.
You know that.
Oh wow!
When you say that,
you sound just like Uesugi!
Hey, don't lump me in
with that jerk!
The two of us are nothing more
than a student and her teacher!
So we need to maintain
some distance!
[FUTARO]
That's exactly what we're doing!
[YOTSUBA]
Bye, Uesugi!
Make sure you read
through that booklet carefully!
That's not happening!
[YOTSUBA] You better
show up in the morning!
Let's make some
great memories together!
Uh. That's right.
My phone.
Uh-oh.
[FUTARO panting]
Raiha! Are you okay?
Big Brother.
I think I might have a fever.
I didn't mean to bother you.
-Sorry.
-No, it's okay.
You've always been
on the frail side,
so I totally understand.
But I'm here now.
And I brought home
some drinks and medicine
to help you feel better, too.
Thank you.
Can I have the medicine now?
-Sure thing.
-Bring me a towel?
-Yup!
-Do my homework for me?
Mm-hmm! Wait, are you trying
to get me to spoil you?
[RAIHA]
Thanks a lot.
Dad says he'll be home from work
as quickly as he can.
Okay.
Anyway, you have a
school trip tomorrow, don't you?
Uh-huh.
Then could I ask you
one last favor?
I want to hear
lots of fun stories
when you get back home, okay?
I'll be all right
on my own until then.
♪
Yeah, you got it.
-Now rest up.
-Mm-hmm.
♪
[FEMALE TEACHER]
Okay, everyone...
[MALE TEACHER]
Itsuki Nakano, a word please?
Uh, Sir?
We've had a last-minute change.
Would you mind
taking over planning
for the test of courage?
Huh?
-[panting]
-[door opens]
Raiha! Are you okay?
Futaro?
Hey, Dad. She's still asleep.
Keep it down, please.
[snoring softly]
[ISANARI] So you've been
taking care of her?
Wait.
The bus for your school trip
must be long gone by now!
You think so?
I didn't care enough to check.
But, hey,
I guess this means I can study
to my heart's content
for the next three days.
[ISANARI] Futaro,
you forgot something.
Sorry, I couldn't
get home before now.
You only get to do this once.
You could still make it,
if you actually tried to.
The bus is gone.
I really don't care.
-Gosh, I sure am hungry!
-[FUTARO/ISANARI] Huh?
Your fever. Is it gone?
Yup, all gone!
Thanks for all your help.
I feel way better
all of a sudden.
You should go on your trip.
Nah, I missed the bus.
[ITSUKI] Sure did.
It left a little while ago.
[FUTARO]
Whoa, why are you here?
I'm solving a problem.
[FUTARO]
Hey, stop it!
Sorry. I need
to borrow Uesugi.
-Okay.
Hang on.
What are you...
[gasps
♪
I don't understand.
-Hey, Futaro.
-You're late.
Are you ready to go?
It sure took you long enough.
They wanted me
to take over for you,
but I wasn't having that.
I'm terrified of ghosts.
So you're gonna have to do it.
♪
If you say so.
I guess I'll come too.
Okay, guys! Road trip!
♪
[QUINTUPLETS]
Quintuplet Game time!
In this game,
we assign each of us
a finger on a person's hand,
and then we try to guess
which one of us
is the finger hiding
behind the other hand.
Doesn't that sound fun?
Okay, who am I?
-Nino.
-Nah, Miku.
-It's me!
-Nino, for sure.
No way, back off!
Touching is against the rules,
you big cheater!
It's Nino.
Sorry, it's Miku.
[FUTARO]
I should've guessed that.
Fine. My turn. Let's go.
Someone's energetic today.
'Cause I haven't traveled
in years!
Not since elementary school!
So I feel like I'm unstoppable!
Makes sense.
Except we've been stopped
by this traffic
for over an hour now.
[wind whistling]
[FUTARO]
Wow, this room is amazing!
[ITSUKI] It only sleeps
four people, though.
You're crazy if you think
I'm about to share
a room with this guy!
They had another big group
show up at the last minute,
so there wasn't
anything else available.
Then let's find another place.
[YOTSUBA]
We can't, the driver went home.
Wait, I know!
He can sleep in that extra room
I saw around the front!
[wind whistling]
What?
He would freeze overnight!
Oh, come on, he'd live.
-I don't think so.
-Huh? What's this?
[ITSUKI]
Only one way to find out, right?
I made you a good luck charm
to keep you safe
while you travel.
I hope you have a good time
at your school camp.
P.S! I'm expecting
a gift in return!
-Raiha.
-[chuckles]
[NINO]
Just hear me out.
[FUTARO]
Yup, I like this place!
Let's stop complaining
and have some fun!
That's it, family meeting.
[NINO] All five of us need
to be extremely careful.
-[YOTSUBA] What for?
-[NINO] Well, you know.
We're going to share a room
with a young man tonight.
And teenage boys
are basically animals.
[FUTARO]
Rawr!
Come on, he's not
gonna try anything.
-Let's do it.
-[squeals]
[ALL gasp]
Um, do what?
I brought some cards.
Let's play.
Is that all?
Oh, that's so old-school.
So what should we play?
[FUTARO]
How about fan-tan?
[ITSUKI]
It is a valid concern, though.
I mean, we are students
and teacher, after all.
[ICHIKA sighs]
-That was an intense card game.
-[MIKU] Yeah.
Want one?
I'm okay for now.
Miku, after what happened,
it looks like
I'll be dancing with him.
Are you sure
you're okay with that?
Yeah. I'm the one who messed
everything up, so it's fine.
[ICHIKA]
All right.
Well, I'll try
to look after him then.
Just leave it
to your oldest sister.
[MIKU]
Keep someone all to myself.
I couldn't do that.
We're five fifths,
and together we're one.
Besides...
if it's Ichika,
then I'm not worried.
[ICHIKA]
Miku says it's okay,
so I guess it is.
♪
[FUTARO]
A smorgasbord!
I want to box it up and save it!
Please don't do that.
[YOTSUBA] Tomorrow,
we're getting rice curry.
It's gonna look pretty sad
after this spread, huh?
I don't know if I want
to eat anything
your team's in charge of.
-Shut up.
-Oh, that's right!
Come to think of it, I haven't
even looked at the schedule yet.
The main events
for day two are:
orienteering, cooking, and then
the test of courage at night.
Day three will have
the optional mountain climb,
skiing, fishing, and last
but not least, the campfire.
[ICHIKA] Why do you have
the whole thing memorized?
Oh, yeah!
I got more info on the campfire!
If you want the legend
to come true,
you should hold hands
at the end!
Not this nonsense again.
What legend?
[NINO]
Eh, don't worry about it.
None of us have a dance partner,
so it's not like
anything'll happen anyway.
[ICHIKA/FUTARO/MIKU gasp]
[FUTARO]
Right, I forgot.
I got roped
into dancing with Ichika.
Not that I believe
in that foolish legend,
but it's an awkward
situation nonetheless.
Ugh. I've got tons
of better things to do
than dance around a fire.
[MIKU]
That's convenient,
since I'm pretty certain
you didn't get any offers.
Oh, I get it,
you're just bitter!
[NINO]
Huh? Hey, who asked you?
Anyway.
They've got
an outdoor bath here.
It looks really nice.
Does that say "mixed"?
What? So not only
are we sharing a room,
we have to share
a bath with him too?
That's unacceptable!
We don't all have to use it
at the same time.
Come on, Nino.
I can't believe
you're too embarrassed
to go into the bath with me.
It's nothing you and I
haven't done before, right?
-You what?
-Wait!
That's not...
Shut up!
[FUTARO laughs]
You know you deserved that.
[ICHIKA/YOTSUBA laugh]
[NINO sighs]
This is great!
[ICHIKA sighs]
It's not a mixed bath.
I guess I misread it.
We don't really take baths
together anymore, do we?
It's been a few years now.
Is it just me or have
your boobs gotten bigger?
No, we're all the same size.
[NINO]
By the way,
something seems off
about you-know-who today.
Oh, I wouldn't worry,
it's probably
'cause he doesn't go
on trips very often.
He's just tired
from studying all night.
It's no big deal.
Even so,
people tend to get flirty
when they're on
a traveler's high like that.
My concern is that
there's barely enough space
in that tiny room of ours
to lay down six futons.
So which one of us
will be sleeping next to him?
-[FUTARO] Rawr!
-[wolf howling]
Nino, come on.
You're overthinking this.
Futaro's our friend,
he wouldn't make a move on us.
She's right! Uesugi's not
interested in us like that!
I assume you're okay
with sleeping next to him, then?
[YOTSUBA]
Huh?
You seem pretty confident
things'll just stay friendly.
So you do it.
Well, on second thought...
I'm not that sure.
Let's see.
Maybe you'd be the best choice.
Hold on!
What makes you say that?
[ITSUKI] I don't know,
because if he came onto you,
you'd be the one to punch him?
[NINO] Ichika! You haven't said
anything, you do it!
I don't see why.
[NINO]
You're just friends, aren't you?
[ICHIKA]
Yeah.
You could say
that Futaro's a friend.
Then it should be you.
[MIKU]
Wait. I know.
Trust me. This way is fair.
[NINO]
I see. That's a good idea.
If nobody wants to.
Then everybody has to.
That's the only
reasonable solution.
Plus, he won't start something
if we're all there.
And if he can't tell who's who.
Well, apparently all that takes
is wearing our hair down.
This is foolproof!
♪
He's out cold.
We should all get some shuteye.
-[ITSUKI] Yeah.
-[ICHIKA] Sounds good.
[birds chirping]
[gasps]
How'd I get here?
This is so weird.
Oh.
[chuckles]
Guess we moved during the night.
This is the second time
I've seen him sleep.
If this gets my heart racing,
then we're not just friends.
Or just partners.
But that's okay, right?
Rise and shine, everyone!
It's time for, uh...
Uh...
[gasps]
[door closes]
[breathing heavily]
[ITSUKI]
No way.
Were they...
-[MALE TEACHER] Nakano?
-Huh?
I thought that was you!
How did you end up
staying at this inn?
♪
[FUTARO] What are the odds
we'd get snowed in and wind up
staying at the same place
as they were?
[STUDENTS chattering]
Can't believe we never saw them.
-Hey, what's with you?
-Huh? Nothing!
I didn't get a good enough look
to be sure what happened.
But one of us
was definitely super close
to Uesugi this morning.
♪
Listen, Ichika.
If you're serious
about your career,
you should think
about taking a break
from high school for a while.
♪
[GIRL 1] Have you picked someone
to dance with
at the campfire?
No, not exactly.
You've got
some high standards, don't you?
I guess so.
♪
[NINO] If only I could meet
somebody like him.
Oh, hey. You know what
the campfire legend is, right?
[GIRL 2] Of course!
It brings couples together!
[GIRL 1]
And I hear it's forever, too!
[YOTSUBA]
Just wait, Uesugi.
I swear you're gonna have fun!
I'll make sure this trip
is one you never forget!
[ITSUKI] We're a teacher
and his students.
Even if a student
develops feelings,
it's the
teacher's responsibility
to set things right again.
Uesugi, it's decided.
I'm treating this camping trip
as an opportunity to figure out
whether or not you're really
up to the challenge
of being our tutor.
[QUINTUPLETS]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[ITSUKI] You're so good
at impersonating us, Miku.
[ICHIKA] Let's see your
Itsuki impression.
[ITSUKI]
I know how this goes.
You're just gonna pig out
on food, right?
[MIKU] Here's her when she
found out Futaro was our tutor.
-Gan!
-[ITSUKI] Gan!
I wasn't ready for that!