♪
[YOTSUBA] And chop!
[grunts]
♪
[laughs]
I could keep this up
all day long!
We've got enough.
You can stop chopping now.
Are you done with this?
I'm tidying up.
[BOY 1]
Uh, yeah!
You gotta love
how on top of things she is.
[NINO]
I think it's probably ready.
Fifteen minutes
and three seconds to go!
Perfectionist much?
What are you putting in, Miku?
Miso. My specialty.
But that pot's for everybody!
I can't believe
you guys ruined the rice!
You shouldn't blame us for that.
It was our first attempt
at cooking it!
I suppose we'll have to
take care of it ourselves then.
Go keep an eye
on the curry, okay?
♪
[MAEDA]
Hey, man.
Don't give me that. I know you
can hear me talkin' to you.
You're actin' like you forgot
who I am already.
Oh no, I remember.
How could I forget you?
[chuckles awkwardly]
Come on, dude,
my name's Maeda!
Are you and Nakano
still doin' okay?
[FUTARO]
Uh. I guess so.
You're lucky you have someone
to dance with at the campfire.
Unlike me.
I couldn't find anybody.
Tell me, do you have any tips
for gettin' a girlfriend?
[FUTARO groans]
This rice can't cook
fast enough.
[MAEDA]
Are you ignorin' me?
-[YOTSUBA] Uesugi!
-Hmm?
I'm about to move
all the test of courage stuff.
[FUTARO]
Yotsuba.
I'm confused.
Weren't you on campfire duty?
Yeah, but I got done early,
so I thought I'd help you, too!
After all,
you're out here camping
in the wilderness with us
when you're used to having
your nose stuck in a book.
You must be way out
of your comfort zone!
[FUTARO]
You got that right.
-Look after the food, Maeda.
-Wha...
I don't take orders from you.
You're not gonna
leave me here, are you?
[FUTARO] The test
of courage is optional.
Why don't you invite
one of the girls from class?
Oh, and we're going all out,
so try not
to wet yourself in fear.
[FUTARO] [growly voice]
Let's play a game!
[BOYS and GIRLS screaming]
[GIRL 1] Ugh, there hasn't been
a single ghost!
They really dropped
the ball this year.
[MAEDA]
Damn it!
I was hoping
the suspension bridge effect
would do me a solid,
but she hasn't gotten scared
a single time yet!
That guy tricked me!
[GIRL 1] He's got
a really mean look on his face!
Okay, now I'm terrified.
-Hyah!
-Yah!
[BOTH screaming]
-[YOTSUBA] We are crushing it!
-[FUTARO chuckles]
This is so awesome!
Who knew dressing up
like a psycho clown
would put some life
in those cold, dead eyes?
[FUTARO] Indeed. I am pleased
to have joined the living.
[cackles]
Huh?
[YOTSUBA]
It's good that you're here.
I was kind of afraid
you wouldn't come.
Let's make sure we don't
leave camp with any regrets!
[giggles]
Ooh! I hear
another group coming!
[FUTARO]
Run for your lives!
Yeah, we're gonna eat
your eyeballs!
Hmm? Futaro?
Yotsuba's here, too.
[FUTARO]
Oh, it's just you.
That was a waste of time.
You already know
the whole gimmick.
[ICHIKA]
Eek, you scared me!
[FUTARO]
Don't bother.
No, you really did!
Hey, is your hair blonde?
What'd you do? Dye it yourself?
No, it's a wig.
Anyway, there's
a precarious cliff up ahead,
so follow the signs and--
Uh, Miku?
Are you even listening?
-Uh?
-Um. Sorry, what?
[FUTARO] I said there's
a dangerous cliff up ahead,
so you need to pay attention
to the signs.
[MIKU]
Yeah, I know.
Are you coming, Ichika?
Uh, sure.
[FUTARO] That's weird.
She seemed kind of cold.
I didn't notice.
Oh yeah, I meant to tell you!
People are saying
you're not scary enough.
You need to make more
of an entrance next time!
[ITSUKI shuddering]
I don't want
to be here anymore, Nino.
Some of my classmates said
it was haunted!
[NINO]
Well, that's obviously not true.
Same goes for that
stupid campfire legend.
It's nothing
but a bunch of nonsense!
What kind of coward gets scared
over such a cheap toy?
I had imagined
our school camp would be
so much more interesting.
But instead, we were forced
to share a room
with that annoying brute
right off the bat.
Whatever. At least nobody got
the moves put on them.
So you're saying
it wasn't you I saw?
-Huh? What wasn't?
-[wood creaking]
[FUTARO]
Study or die!
[ITSUKI/NINO whimpering]
[screaming]
I can't take anymore!
[NINO] Itsuki, calm down!
It's not real!
Uh-oh. I think
we might've overdone it.
Huh? Which way
did they run off to?
Miku, you finally got
to see Futaro.
Why were you in such a hurry
to leave though?
[MIKU]
There's something wrong with me.
[ICHIKA]
What?
Well, he's supposed
to be tutoring all five of us.
What do you think
about Futaro, Ichika?
Tell me the truth.
[NINO]
Itsuki? Where did you go?
This way, right? I'm not sure.
My phone! Oh! Why me?
School camp is supposed
to be fun!
Why am I out here all alone?
[wind gusting]
♪
[whimpering]
[rustling]
No!
[grunts]
[groans]
That hurt.
Someone rescue me, please.
[FUTARO]
Are you okay?
What'd you scream for? You hurt?
No way. Could it be?
Huh?
[NINO] You're him, the boy
I saw in that picture!
You're talking nonsense.
Okay, we should get going.
Come with me.
Hold on, what's happening?
[ripping]
[gasps]
Oh no! I'm so sorry!
Great, she's gonna kill me.
What the...
I didn't mean to do that.
She's unusually docile.
[NINO] Please!
Will you tell me your name?
Sorry, it's just...
I'm pretty sure
I've seen you in a photograph,
and I thought you were
really handsome.
Photograph?
[NINO] I knew
there were students
from other high schools
at this camp,
but I never thought
in a million years
I'd meet his relative here.
Wha...
Who is this?
[FUTARO]
Um, he's one of my relatives.
Seriously?
[gasps]
Right, it's because of the wig!
She thinks I'm the guy
in the photo.
I mean, I am,
but she doesn't know that!
Crap. Should I
just come clean?
Explain to her that
we're the same person?
Nah, she'll find a way
to use it against me.
Better keep up the lie. Okay!
Well, if you just go straight,
you'll find a bigger path.
See ya!
[NINO]
No, wait!
I can't find my sister.
I was hoping you could maybe
help me look for her.
Uh--
[growling]
[screaming]
[sighs]
Geez, Uesugi.
You've been gone forever!
[NINO]
So, your name's Kintaro, is it?
Yeah.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Where the hell
are you, Itsuki?
Come on!
He's exactly my type!
♪
Hey! I sure could use a drink!
Huh?
I wanna break the law!
Even though I'm underage,
I drink lots of alcohol!
Did that work?
Does she hate me now?
Oh wow, you're such a bad boy.
Not what I intended!
Itsuki...
Uh, I mean your sister
probably went to the campsite.
Polaris is five lengths
below the Big Dipper,
so north should be
that way from here.
That's enough info to get back.
You're a really smart guy!
There's nothing I admire more
than an intellectual!
[FUTARO]
That's a lie.
[NINO]
You're so much more attractive
than someone
who's always bragging
and showing off
their perfect grades.
Huh. I didn't know
people actually did that.
How could you not know.
You're related
to someone who does.
Hey, wait.
Could I look at you closer?
Um, what is it?
[NINO]
I knew it!
There's a bruise
on your forehead!
That? It's just a scrape.
I'm sure it'll heal on its own.
Sorry, that's unacceptable.
One of my sisters
is always coming home
with bumps and bruises.
There, much better.
[FUTARO]
I don't get her.
-[eerie wailing]
-[NINO whimpering]
Hey, do you hear a creepy voice
from that way?
My sister did say
this forest was haunted.
Come on, that's ridiculous.
I-I know what'll help!
I have this good-luck charm
with me!
It'll protect us
from all kinds of evil!
[eerie wailing continues]
[BOTH gasp]
-[FUTARO] No, no, no!
-Huh? Hey!
Wait a minute, Kintaro.
Don't leave me here all alone.
This place is really scary!
No, it's not. Look at me.
I'm not scared,
not even a little!
Where'd the path go?
[NINO]
Ugh, this guy's kind of a wimp.
What a disappointment!
There's a path over here, too.
Huh?
[NINO] Look! We're at
the edge of the woods!
Stop, you idiot,
you can't go that way!
Huh? What do you mean, I can't?
♪
[FUTARO straining]
-[FUTARO] Damn it!
-No!
-[NINO straining]
-[FUTARO] Uh!
[FUTARO panting]
[whimpers softly]
You saved my life.
That's my line.
Thanks a lot.
Still no sign
of your sister, though.
I'm pretty sure
she must've gone back.
-What's wrong?
-Um...
I don't think I can move yet.
I'm too scared.
Could you please hold my hand?
Huh?
I'm just saying,
there's no telling
what might jump out at us
next time, you know?
Sorry, we're
practically strangers.
That's way too forward!
Forget I said it.
[FUTARO]
All right.
♪
Uh?
I'm telling you, this good-luck
charm is all-powerful.
If you hang onto it,
the monsters'll never get you.
And I've heard it can
even grant your wishes.
Use it wisely.
[NINO]
Will you be here tomorrow too?
I'd like to see you again.
Uh... Uh-huh.
[NINO] Well, tomorrow night,
my school's doing
this big campfire gathering.
There's even a legend that goes
with the folk dance we do.
They say that
if you're holding hands
with someone
when the music ends,
then you're destined
to end up together.
[FUTARO]
Oh, really?
A lot of couples
have started going out
just because of this one night.
Even the shy kids do it,
but they usually find
a quiet spot
where no one can see.
[FUTARO]
Sounds like a big deal.
Personally, I think
it's overblown and childish.
But still...
I'd really like you
to come dance with me, Kintaro.
Um, I...
I hope you'll be there.
[leaves rustling]
[eerie wailing]
There's that voice again!
It's coming this way!
[wailing continues]
[crying]
-What?
-What? It's Itsuki!
[NINO]
Get it together!
[ITSUKI]
Nino!
I've been so lonely
and scared this whole time!
You were the one doing
the scaring out here!
Let's get back to camp.
[ITSUKI]
Uh, okay. Although...
I'm surprised you
were okay by yourself.
Well, I wasn't alone.
I was with...
[ITSUKI]
What's the matter?
[chuckles]
[NINO]
I'll see you soon.
[FUTARO]
Now what?
So, you want to know
what I think about Futaro?
I think he's in the middle
of his awkward phase.
I mean, the poor little fella's
so off-the-wall
and unbalanced, you know.
I'd hate for him to enter
adulthood like that!
That's not what I mean.
I want to know how you feel.
[ICHIKA]
Miku...
I think you and I should
trade spots for the dance.
You seem pretty nervous.
But I can't.
It's only fair for you
to dance with him.
Don't give yourself
things to regret.
These days aren't going
to last forever, right?
[NINO fawning]
I know camp's not going
to last forever,
but I sure wish it would!
You're in a good mood.
Did something happen today?
I'm not telling you!
[FUTARO] Well, this is
a bit of a quagmire.
I could easily just dance
with her in disguise
and call it done,
except I've already committed
to dancing with Ichika!
I can't clone myself.
The only option is
to tell the truth.
Huh? Where is she?
♪
[ICHIKA]
What's going on, Futaro?
Uh--
Ichika. Miku.
Perfect timing.
I wanted to ask you--
Whoops! I have
to go do something.
You kids have fun, okay?
She's acting funny.
Anyway, I'm glad
you're still here, Miku.
Nino around?
-Not a clue.
-Uh...
Her too?
I guess they all hate me
more than I thought.
[ITSUKI]
You just now realized that?
Here's a tip.
If you don't want
to make things worse,
then maybe stop acting like
you have something to hide.
No idea what
you're talking about.
♪
[FUTARO]
I am making it worse.
I need to get myself
out of this mess, and fast!
[YOTSUBA]
Thanks for helping.
It would take forever
with just me!
[FUTARO]
So we're moving all these logs?
[YOTSUBA]
Yup!
They were keeping them in here
to protect them from the snow.
The team's working really hard
to get ready
for the campfire tomorrow!
'Kay.
[strains, groans]
[YOTSUBA] I'd expect a guy
to be stronger than this.
[FUTARO grunts]
[YOTSUBA] Uh, I mean,
I'm still super grateful
that you're willing
to lend a hand anyway!
Well, I owe you one.
The test of courage
wouldn't have been
half as good without you.
Yeah, I agree!
Especially since
I had to take care
of all of the scaring myself
while you were MIA!
[FUTARO] Is it just me,
or do the five of them
seem extremely unhappy
with me lately?
I'd better hurry
and regain their trust.
I don't want anything
to endanger my job.
'Kay, next one!
This is great!
We're working and exercising!
Whew. I'm dying.
Have I always been
this much of a wimp?
[GIRL 2]
Hey, Nakano, could I trouble you
for a quick second?
There should be a key
next to the shed door.
[FUTARO]
And hup!
This is heavy!
Oh hey!
Thought you were
someone else for a second.
You weren't assigned
to this job, were you?
Uh, where's Yotsuba?
Hey, wait a sec.
If Ichika and Yotsuba
are both here,
it might be
the perfect chance for me
to get back
in their good graces!
It's cold.
I should've worn a jacket.
[FUTARO]
Body, don't fail me now!
Let's set my communication
stat to maximum!
I wanted to help Yotsuba.
Now, let's do this!
By the way, did you enjoy
the test of courage?
Huh? Uh, yeah,
it was pretty scary.
That is great to hear!
As a member of the committee,
I welcome your feedback!
Although, part of the reason
I was so scared
was because I wasn't
a hundred percent sure
whether you would be able
to pull it off or not.
Well, I can't argue
with that logic, now can I?
[laughs]
Wait a second, Futaro.
You're acting way stranger
than usual.
Sorry, what about this
comes off as strange to you?
Well, for one thing,
the Futaro I know
would never go out of his way
to make small talk.
Now, tell me
what's bothering you.
I see.
You're freaking out
because you're scared
somebody's gonna hate you.
[FUTARO]
I wouldn't say that, exactly.
Aw, our sensitive little Futaro.
I just told you, that's not it!
[ICHIKA] Don't worry,
big sis'll help you practice.
What do you mean
by "practice"?
Miku's better at this
than I am, but...
"Can't you see this is heavy.
Stop whining and help me,
you useless jerk?"
Nino!
"What are you
standing around here for?
"Don't you think
you'd better start
taking your job
more seriously?"
That's Itsuki!
Go ahead, answer them.
Oh! Uh, okay!
I'm sorry, Itsuki.
Your beauty distracted me.
Ew, that was so creepy.
[FUTARO straining, grunting]
[ICHIKA] Just try to act
like a normal human.
Actually,
there's a trick to it.
When you're with Nino,
be as strong as her.
When you're with Itsuki,
be nice.
And speak in your own words.
Oh, and you can be nice
when you're talking to me, too.
Be nice, huh?
I can remember that.
I'm glad I got to talk
to her first.
She's definitely not
the oldest for nothing.
She looks at me
and all of her sisters
objectively and rationally.
Okay, Next is Mik--
Something wrong?
No, not at all.
[FUTARO]
Guess that's the last of them.
[ICHIKA] We're all set
for tomorrow's campfire.
Looks that way.
Have you talked to Miku lately?
Yeah. She told me
about the dance thing.
Don't worry.
[FUTARO] I still can't believe
that played out the way it did.
[ICHIKA] I agree, it's pretty
embarrassing, huh?
You think we should practice
ahead of time?
[FUTARO]
Ichika or Nino.
If I really have
to choose between them.
Let's call it off.
I mean, this only happened
because of a misunderstanding.
And if you ask me,
that whole legend thing
is kind of obnoxious.
Maeda won't like it,
but you can deal
with that, right?
I mean, think about it.
If people saw you
dancing with me,
that probably wouldn't be
very good for your reputation,
would it?
Huh? You're crying!
Oh gosh.
I'm okay. Really.
Can I put this thing
down, though?
[GIRL 3] Come on! Let's get this
done and head back to the inn.
[GIRL 4] Oh wait.
Someone already moved them.
[GIRL 3]
Looks that way.
They made really good time!
-Yeah.
-[YOTSUBA] Excuse me!
Have either of you
seen Uesugi around here?
[GIRL 3]
Wait. Uesugi?
-Um...
-[GIRL 4] Haven't seen him.
Aw, man. This brings
back memories, doesn't it?
Is there a reason
we're hiding though?
[YOTSUBA]
Yeah...
[FUTARO]
Be nice. Right.
Nobody can see now.
Uh... that's a weird thing
to say, huh?
[lock clicks]
-Hold on.
-Was that...
[FUTARO]
It's not locked though, right?
Surely not.
[ICHIKA]
Wasn't there a key here?
[laughter]
[FUTARO]
Well, that just happened.
[QUINTUPLETS]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[ICHIKA] So that blonde guy's
your type, huh, Nino?
[NINO]
Hair dye is against the rules.
[MIKU]
He looks trashy.
[ICHIKA] I bet he doesn't have
any kind of future.
[NINO]
I know, right?
I guess I'll end up
supporting him, won't I?
[awkward laughter]