[slurping]
♪
Oh, hey, good morning!
-Hey there.
-Come on.
No thoughts
on my winter uniform?
You're fishing
for compliments this early?
I'll settle for walking
to class together.
[FUTARO] I'd rather not.
You tend to stand out.
[giggles]
By the way,
I told the rest of the girls
about my job yesterday.
They had a lot of questions.
[ITSUKI]
Like, a real actress?
[YOTSUBA]
When's the movie come out?
I'm sure.
Still, though.
It's a huge load off!
[chuckles]
[TEACHER] The midterm exams
begin next week.
And by the way,
in case you didn't know,
scores below thirty count
as failing, like always.
So check your work,
and check it twice.
I'm not too worried.
Guess it's that time.
♪
[FUTARO]
Itsuki.
What do you want?
Wow!
I can't believe
I caught you studying
while we're on a break.
-Good!
-[gasps]
What?
And I hear you study
after school, too.
You're the most diligent one.
It was easy to pick up on that
since we're both
in the same class.
Do you really think so?
Yep! But you're still
dumb as a rock!
You should stop
being so stubborn.
If you get off your high horse
and join the study group,
I'm sure even you could make
your grades better.
Uh-huh!
I think so too!
There's only so much
I can accomplish
by myself, you know?
Mm-hmm.
[ITSUKI] Could you please
help me with this question?
Be glad to.
Sure, I'll help.
Come see me
in the staff room later.
[ITSUKI]
I'll do that, ma'am.
-Thank you.
-[FUTARO groans]
[mocking]
I'm not giving up yet.
Now! Nino!
[GIRLS]
Huh?
What's up?
Ready for the midterms?
Let's go, girls.
[GIRL 1]
Nino, he's talking to you.
[NINO]
Don't mind him, he's a stalker.
[GIRL 2]
Gross!
Hey! This is far from over!
You were into it at
the festival, so what changed?
-[NINO] Ehh.
-[GIRLS] Huh?
Come on, just think about it!
We can do it anywhere,
your place or mine!
One more time!
Give me one more chance!
I know what I'm doing, okay?
I can teach you so many things!
I swear, you'll be satisfied!
Well? Are you convinced? Huh?
Argh! Just stop talking.
Learn how to choose
your words, you creep!
[FUTARO]
Aahh!
[ICHIKA laughs]
That looks like it hurt.
[MIKU]
You okay?
Yeah. Forget that--
Uesugi! Pop Quiz!
Do you notice anything
that's different
about my appearance today?
I assume all of you are aware
that midterms
are coming up soon.
Rude!
-Listen.
-I'll give you a clue,
it's above the neck!
Unless you improve
your performance,
there's no way
you'll survive.
Ta-da!
The answer is, my ribbon has
a different pattern than usual!
Apparently checks
are totally in style right now!
Well, since you've got checks
for all the erroneous answers
you wrote,
you're high-fashion.
Woohoo, I'm such a trendsetter!
[laughing]
Ichika. You've got nothing
to laugh about.
I mean, at least Yotsuba's
willing to improve herself.
There's only one week
before the midterms,
and you slackers are gonna
be ready if it kills ya!
-What?
-In every subject!
You hear that? Even in...
English?
Miku's studying
her weakest subject,
and I didn't even have
to force her to?
Is something wrong?
[MIKU]
I'm fine.
I just felt like trying
for once, that's all.
Wow.
[YOTSUBA] All right,
now I'm good and motivated!
Yeah!
Inside voices!
[ICHIKA/YOTSUBA]
Sorry.
♪
I'm so beat!
Yeah, I can't wait
to go home and crash.
♪
[FUTARO]
Damn.
Guess after-school sessions
won't be enough.
How much can we cram in
during the weekend?
[blows]
[shouting]
What are you doing?
You don't expect us
to work more, do you?
It's not like
we're gonna get expelled
if we fail a midterm.
We'll all give it
our best shot, okay?
Just be patient with us.
But I mean, if you wanted us
to try harder,
you could give us an incentive.
Ooh! I know what!
That fruit parfait
by the station!
I want matcha parfait.
You're right,
that does sound pretty good!
I'll text the others
and have them meet us there.
[FUTARO]
What?
But I thought you couldn't wait
to get back home.
Maybe I should let them do
their own thing.
[YOTSUBA]
Uesugi!
Hurry your butt up or we'll eat
all the parfait without you!
♪
[ITSUKI]
Hey!
-Hold it right there!
-Huh?
[panting]
How could you!
What kind of person would decide
to go home in that situation?
Huh?
You were supposed
to have parfaits with them!
Nah, I have to study.
I don't understand.
You chased me down
just to say that?
Of course not! Hold on a second.
Somebody wants to talk to you.
[FUTARO]
Me?
Hey, it's me.
I'm putting him on now.
Uh, hello?
[MAN]
You must be Uesugi.
Thank you for looking
after my daughters.
Hey there, Pops!
Don't mention it!
I should be thanking you!
[FATHER] I don't recall
giving you permission
to call me "Pops."
I can't hear what he's saying,
but I guarantee you
he didn't like that.
[FATHER]
I'm sorry I haven't been able
to make an appearance at home,
but I trust that
the tutoring job
has been going well thus far?
Oh, yeah. As a matter of fact,
we're nose-deep
in our textbooks now!
Okay, Itsuki, I'll help you.
Just wait till
I get off the phone.
I have utmost confidence in all
five of your daughters, sir.
I know they'll succeed.
[FATHER]
Well, that's a relief.
I hear the midterms
are just around the corner,
so I'm glad
you're making progress.
This may sound a bit harsh,
but I refuse to accept
a negative result from you.
In other words, if even
one of my daughters receives
a failing grade
on her midterms,
I'll have no choice
but to ask you
to tender your resignation
as their tutor.
Immediately.
[FUTARO]
Fired?
[FATHER]
I wish you the best of luck.
Wait, sir, please reconsider.
It's too early to give
such an ultimatum!
Oh, no. Aah!
[ITSUKI] Don't even think
about throwing my phone!
Sorry. Take it.
So, what did my father want
to discuss with you?
Oh, you know,
just regular chit-chat.
[ITSUKI] And that's enough
to make you sweat bullets?
Well, I suggest
you forget about me
and start worrying
about yourself.
I hope you'll be adequately
prepared for your midterm exams.
[ITSUKI]
Uh, yeah, no problem.
That doesn't inspire confidence.
You got a bad mark
on that quiz today, didn't you?
You looked at that?
[sighs]
[FUTARO]
Well, there's my answer.
I'd better not discourage her.
I'm sure she's giving it
her best, right?
I'm here for you, Itsuki.
Let me know if there's anything
I can help you with.
Ugh. What's your deal?
Are you trying to say
that you don't believe me?
[FUTARO]
Oh, great, now she's angry!
[ITSUKI] Like I told you before,
I don't need your help.
No, your work is great, but you
can always be more efficient!
That's all I meant.
I can teach you some tricks!
[grunts]
Why can't you be more
like Miku and Ichika?
You've probably
forgotten this by now,
but I was the first one
to ask you to help me.
And then you acted like a jerk
and turned me down.
I have nothing to learn
from someone like that.
But the exams
are almost here!
You really think
you'll pass without me?
It's fine!
Even if it's too late
to ace the midterms,
I can still pass my grade.
That won't be good enough!
If you fail this time,
it's over!
Your grades are my job!
Now quit fussing
and do as I say!
You're the only person
who's fussing here.
You should want to do better
in school, Itsuki!
All right?
So why don't you just shut up
and listen to me for once?
Uh, sorry!
I shouldn't have.
I was starting to respect you.
Just the slightest bit.
But I'm starting to realize
that I made a mistake.
Money.
That's all you're after.
[gasps]
♪
Yeah, so what?
I need money!
What kind of moron
would put up
with an obnoxious little jerk
like you for free?
We're nothing but a herd
of cash-cows to you?
Fine. Then you don't need
to torture yourself
trying to teach me anymore!
Okay, but don't you come
crying to me
when you flunk out, got it?
[ITSUKI]
Deal.
Even if I'm kicked
out of school.
I don't care.
You'll never be my tutor again!
And I'm never teaching you
another measly thing!
Why did I say
something so stupid?
[FUTARO]
Fired!
My neck is on the line!
This is no time
to start a fight!
I should just come clean.
-[YOTSUBA] Uesugi!
-Mm?
Check me out,
I just got married!
Gimme that gift money!
Oh, right, here you go.
[YOTSUBA]
Mama needs a new house!
[MIKU]
Okay, my turn next.
Even in a board game,
I'm still poor.
We don't have time
for this dumb game!
Break's over! Let's crack
those textbooks open!
Huh?
But we studied our butts off
all day long!
Yeah, my poor noggin's
about to explode.
We can't overdo it.
You have a point, but...
[MIKU]
Futaro.
You're more
high-strung than usual.
Does that mean
we're that far behind?
[FUTARO]
Well, no.
It's just...
Hey! Look at all you
lazy bums,
playing board games
instead of studying!
I want in.
I'll just take
your spot for a while.
-What were you saying?
-Huh?
Come on. Tell us.
Oh, it's nothing important!
Ew! You're, like, super poor!
[FUTARO] Wow, better not
tell her anything.
If she found out
what was going on,
I think I know
how she'd react.
[giggling]
You want to play too?
Itsuki?
About yesterday.
I can't talk.
I have a ton
of studying to do.
[FUTARO]
Hey, wait a second!
Okay. You're all done lecturing
us for the day, aren't you?
Time to go home!
[FUTARO]
Why, what's the hurry?
[NINO] Beat it!
You're off the clock!
Nino. Hey. Stop.
Please. Geez.
Damn, pushing and shoving
is getting us nowhere!
[ICHIKA]
Not so fast, Futaro!
-Don't go back on your word.
-[FUTARO] Huh?
You promised us you were
gonna stay here overnight
so that we could get
some more studying in.
-[FUTARO] What?
-[NINO] What?
[FUTARO]
Nice tub.
I still don't understand
why Ichika decided
to rescue me like that, though.
Well, despite everything.
I can see the light
at the end of the tunnel.
She'll come around.
I just need more time.
[NINO]
Uesugi? It's me, Itsuki.
I was talking to Ichika,
and she said that
you had something
you wanted to tell me.
So, what's on your mind?
Who, me?
There's nothing I need to say.
[NINO]
Oh, really? Okay, then.
Wait, I was just kidding!
I'm glad you stopped by!
Just get to the point
or I'm leaving.
♪
[grunting]
Sorry for yesterday.
I let my emotions
get the best of me.
I hope you'll allow me
to continue teaching you.
[NINO]
What happened, exactly?
If any of you don't pass
your midterms...
then I'll lose my job
as your tutor.
[NINO]
I see. So that's what it was.
Whoa, you can't just
barge in here!
Why not? You've already
seen me naked,
so consider us even.
I've been wondering
what all this tension is about
with you and Itsuki.
So you're out of here
if we don't pass, then?
That's quite
an interesting tidbit.
[YOTSUBA] Uesugi's been
in the tub for a while now.
It's not every day
he gets to use the same bath
as five beautiful ladies.
[MIKU]
Bath.
Go check on him.
Unh-unh.
He's staying here overnight,
so if you wanted
to make a move on him,
you couldn't ask
for a better opportunity.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
[YOTSUBA]
Hey, Uesugi!
Welcome back!
I'm sorry to keep
you guys waiting.
Ready to pick up
where we left off?
[gasps]
Uh, you're welcome
to join, Nino.
I don't see any need for that.
[FUTARO]
Great. Nino would love it
if one of them failed
and I got fired.
That girl is never going
to apply herself,
unless she applies herself
to not studying.
What do I do?
Question, teacher!
-This problem here.
-Huh?
Which one?
Sorry, let's scooch over!
-[MIKU] Uh!
-[FUTARO] Ahh!
-Hey!
-What?
Miku needs your help
with something, too.
Ichika!
Oh, yeah, I can answer that!
-Ask me anything, guys!
-[YOTSUBA] 'Kay!
Yes!
Can you tell me
a synonym for argument?
That is an excellent question!
How about "debate"?
You can even spell it
using hiragana!
See, it's de, ba, and te!
You'll see that one
on the exam for sure.
You hear that, Nino?
I'm not going anywhere!
I actually have
a question as well.
What kind of girls
do you like, Futaro?
[ALL gasp]
Is that really relevant
right now?
[YOTSUBA]
Yes, sir!
Because I'm interested
in knowing the same thing, sir!
To what end?
Well, if you want
to know that badly,
I guess I can
teach you my criteria.
Behold, I have a top three!
However,
I'll only reveal one
for every page you finish.
♪
[FUTARO] They're so easy
to manipulate.
♪
Okay! I finished one!
[FUTARO]
Good!
Number three.
[imitating drumroll]
Bam!
Always cheerful!
Hey. I'm done.
[FUTARO] Number two.
[imitating engine running]
Bam! Good at cooking!
-'Kay, I'm finished.
-[FUTARO] Great.
Number one.
[imitating drumroll]
[heart beating rapidly]
Bam!
She cares about her big brother!
You're just talking
about your sister!
[RAIHA giggles]
[FUTARO]
Oh, hey, Nino.
If you're so interested,
why don't you join us?
You're making so much noise,
how could I not overhear you?
Wait, don't leave!
You made us go through
all that just to say Raiha?
Ugh, no fair!
[MIKU]
That's not me.
Look, I'm just not
interested in dating.
You satisfied now?
♪
Ooh! That's cool!
Miku's already finished
with her work.
You're supposed to praise people
when they've done
a good job, Futaro.
Here, I'll show you how.
"Well done, Miku."
So, is your heart racing?
-Not really.
-[grunts]
Yotsuba, come check him!
[YOTSUBA] Yay!
[giggles]
-Stop it, Yotsuba!
-I'm gonna get you!
[FUTARO]
Ugh, leave me alone!
[YOTSUBA]
Not happening!
I said knock it off!
♪
[heart beating rapidly]
[YOTSUBA]
His heart's totally racing!
Because I was running around!
[ITSUKI]
You guys are so loud.
I know there's five of you,
but you'd think a study group
would be quieter.
Sorry.
[FUTARO] It's hard to apologize
now that she's right here.
Miku, is it okay
if I borrow your headphones?
I don't mind, but why?
[ITSUKI] To drown out
some of this racket.
[FUTARO]
Unbelievable.
Itsuki!
Are you sure
I can depend on you?
I just don't want to do anything
that'll hold you back.
Look at the stars, Futaro!
They're so pretty!
Huh?
We should take a little break.
Come on out!
Um, wait a second!
[MIKU]
Ietsuna, Tsunayoshi, Ienobu.
[YOTSUBA]
Got it.
Ietsuna, Tsunayoshi, Ietsuna.
[MIKU]
You said one twice.
Okay. Ienobu. Ietsuyoshi?
Now you're combining them.
♪
[ICHIKA] So, are you fighting
with Itsuki?
[FUTARO]
No more than usual.
[ICHIKA]
Ha, true!
It's like you two
are oil and water.
You just can't
coexist peacefully.
I think it's because
you're too much alike.
[FUTARO]
Too much alike?
You guys are quints.
I guess you're right.
I don't know, today seemed
kinda different.
I think it's better
when the two of you argue
like good friends do.
-[FUTARO] That's a paradox.
-[ICHIKA] Is it?
Itsuki's being stubborn,
that's all.
Aren't you doing
the same thing?
She's always been
kind of an awkward girl.
It's hard for her
to express herself.
I'm sure she's suffering
right now.
I'll do whatever I can
to help her feel better,
but there are some things
that are gonna have
to come from you.
So, are you in?
Huh.
The five of you were born
on the same day,
so I thought this didn't make
any difference.
♪
But you really are
the big sister.
-Why'd you pet me?
-I, uh...
I was just taking a page
out of your book!
Whatever, it's cold,
we should go back inside.
Cold?
♪
I don't... think it is.
Here. You can borrow
my bedroom for the night.
Is this really
for one person?
Not bad.
[ICHIKA]
Mm, where you goin'?
[MIKU]
Bathroom.
♪
Okay?
Why me?
[QUINTUPLETS]
Quintuplet Trivia!
[ICHIKA] Out of all five of us,
Itsuki's the one
that eats the most.
[ITSUKI] Hey, don't make up
lies about me!
All I've eaten today is a bowl
of katsudon, thank you!
[YOTSUBA]
Oh, yeah!
[MIKU] But it's eight o'clock
in the morning.