In the ancient times,
the land lay covered with deep forests,
where, from ages long past,
dwelt the spirits of the gods.
PRINCESS
MONONOKE
Yakul! Come on, boy!
Ashitaka!
Just in time! The wise woman wants
everybody back to the village at once.
- We just came from Ji-San.
- Did he see something?
Yes, in the forest.
- The birds have all gone!
- And the animals, too!
I'll go to the watchtower to see Ji-San.
You hurry back home.
All right!
Something's there.
Ji-San, did you see it too?
I did. It isn't human.
The wise woman's calling
everyone back to the village.
There, look!
- It's some kind of demon!
- A demon?
Run, Yakul, run!
It's headed for the village.
I must stop it.
Prince Ashitaka, wait!
Be careful, the thing is cursed!
Don't let it touch you!
Here, Yakul!
Calm your fury, oh mighty Lord!
Whatever you may be, god or demon,
please, leave us in peace!
- A monster!
- Come on!
Go back!
Please leave our village alone!
Stop, please, stop!
- He killed it!
- Ashitaka!
- Fetch the wise woman!
- Don't put out the fire yet!
Ashitaka!
Kaya, don't touch it! This wound is evil.
The prince has been hurt.
Where is the wise woman?
Keep away from him!
Everyone stay back!
- What shall we do?
- Pour this over his wound, slowly.
Nameless god of rage and hate,
I bow before you.
A mound will be raised
and funeral rites performed
on this ground where you have fallen.
Pass on in peace
and bear us no hatred.
Disgusting little creatures,
soon all of you will feel my hate
and suffer as I have suffered.
I'm afraid this is very bad.
The stones tell me the boar-god came
from far to the west.
He had some kind of a poison inside
him, driving him mad.
A poisonous hatred that consumed his
heart and flesh
and turned him into a demon-monster.
- Prince Ashitaka.
- Yes?
Show everyone your right arm.
What does it mean?
My Prince,
are you prepared to learn what fate
the stones have foretold you?
Yes. I was prepared the moment I let
my arrow fly.
The infection will spread throughout
your whole body, bone and flesh alike.
It will cause you great pain,
then Kill you.
Is there no way we can stop it?
He got that wound defending our village
and saving our lives!
Do we just sit and watch him die?
You cannot alter your fate, my Prince.
However, you can rise to meet lit,
If you choose.
Look at this.
This iron ball
was found in the boar's body.
This is what hurt him so.
It shattered his bones
and burned its way deep inside him.
This is what turned him into a demon.
There is evil at work in the land to
the west, Prince Ashitaka.
It's your fate to go there so you can
see with eyes unclouded by hate.
You may find a way to lift the curse,
you understand?
Yes.
We are the last of the Emishi.
It's five hundred years
since the Emperor destroyed our tribe
and drove the remnants of our people
to the east.
Some managed to survive here for all
these years.
But the blood of our tribe has grown
weaker and thinner
with each generation.
Now our last prince must cut his hair
and leave us, never to return.
Sometimes I think the gods
are laughing at us.
Our laws forbid us from
watching you go, Ashitaka.
Whatever comes to pass now,
you are dead to us forever. Farewell.
What are you doing here?
You know it's forbidden.
Do you think I care about that?
I came to give you this so you won't
forget your little sister.
Your crystal dagger? I can't take this.
Please keep it with you, brother,
to protect you.
You must take it. I want you to have it.
So you won't forget.
Kaya, you know
I could never forget you.
A battle?
They're unarmed! Move in!
- Look, up there on the hill!
- It's a warrior!
You, stop!
My arm! What's happening to me?
Hurry! Stop him before he gets away!
Let me pass! I'm warning you!
A demon?
The mark's getting bigger.
Are you selling soup or donkey piss?
There he is now.
Will this be enough?
What are you trying to pull?
This isn't money.
Give me back my rice, you little thief!
Excuse me, but might I inspect that?
My God! This is a lump of pure gold,
you silly woman!
However, if it's money you want,
I'll pay for the rice
and take this nugget off your hands.
What do you say?
Is there a money changer who could tell
us how much this is worth?
No? All right.
Now, I'm just a monk, but I'd say
three bags of rice at least.
- Wait a minute. Where are you going?
- Give me back my gold!
Hey!
What's your hurry?
You can't just rush off now.
Don't you even think of thanking me.
It was my pleasure.
In fact, I should be thanking you.
You see, I was caught in that battle.
I saw what you did to that samurai.
You fight like a demon.
You noticed we're being followed.
That's what we get for waving that gold
nugget around.
They'll wait till we're asleep
and then they'll slit our throats.
Shall we run?
So, the demon-monster turned out to be
a giant boar.
I followed its trail westward through
the mountains
to where the samurai were attacking
those villagers, but then...
You lost it. That's life.
See this place here?
When I came here last, a few years
back, this was a lovely little village.
But then there must have been a flood
or a landslide, or a fire.
The only sure thing is that everybody
is dead.
These days, there are angry ghosts all
around us.
Dead from wars, sickness, starvation,
and nobody cares.
You say you're under a curse, so what?
So's the whole damn world.
Mmm... Delicious.
I was wrong to fight in that village.
Two men are dead because of me.
Samurai thugs.
You win some, you lose some.
Hand me your bowl.
My point is, everybody dies.
Some now, some later.
Beautiful bowl.
I've seen one other like it.
Have you ever
heard of the Emishi people?
They were said to ride red elks.
They also used stone arrowheads,
just like you.
The most important things do not
get defeated by death.
My master told me that once, you know.
Well, here's your rice. Eat up my boy!
Have you ever come across
anything like this before?
Is this...
It came from the giant boar.
It was inside him.
I'm sure it was that little ball of
iron that killed him.
There's a place high in the mountains
far to the west of here.
It's where the spirit of the forest dwells,
but it's a dangerous place for humans.
To enter there is certain death.
The spirit of the forest?
The beasts there are all giants,
like they were at the dawn of time.
See you there, my friend.
The sooner we get this rice home,
the sooner we eat. Let's move!
Coming this way! Wolves!
Don't let the oxen panic! Stay calm!
Take up your positions.
Keep your powder dry.
Make sure you wait for them to come
within range.
Ready? And fire!
Second round, fire!
That was it? They weren't so big.
They're just pups. Wait till
you see their mother. Where are they?
It's Moro!
Come on.
We killed her!
You forget she is a god.
It will take more than that.
She certainly did some damage.
We move out now.
What about the men
she pushed over the cliff?
They're dead. Let's get the living home.
He's still breathing.
Hang on!
My name is Ashitaka!
I've traveled far from lands to the east.
Are you ancient gods? Have I come to
the realm of the spirit of the forest?
Go away!
A Kodama! I never thought I'd see one
of them here.
Easy, there. You don't want to make
your injuries worse, do you?
He's a tree spirit. He brings good luck.
It's a sign this forest is healthy.
But they'll lead their lord and master
right to us!
Who do you mean?
Those wolves I just saw?
No, I mean a real monster,
like a huge enormous deer...
Where did it go?
If Yakul is not afraid,
we have nothing to worry about here.
Would you be kind enough to grant us
passage through your forest?
Sir, I really think we should turn
around now.
Did I mention no human has ever
made it through the woods alive?
There's a lovely trail back across the
river.
The current is too swift for us
to get across
and your friend's injuries are very bad.
If we don't get him back soon,
he doesn't stand a chance.
Little fellow, are you showing us
the way or getting us more lost?
Please, sir. I'm pretty sure they're
not trying to help us get home.
My God, there's thousands of them!
Look at that, it must be their mother.
A fine old tree.
The tracks of those wolves
and the girl with them!
This place must be
where the four of them live.
Sir, I think maybe we took
a wrong turn somewhere.
This is a place for gods and demons!
I think we're safe. We'll rest a bit.
More tracks?
Whatever made these made them
recently.
Sir! What's going on? Are you all right?
Sir, what just happened there?
You went white as a sheet
all of a sudden.
I warned you about this place.
Did you see anything just then?
- Like what?
- Forget it.
Hang on just a little longer.
You're almost home.
I failed her.
It's gone.
That's strange.
Suddenly he doesn't feel heavy at all.
My arm! It doesn't hurt!
Yes! Ouch! It's still broken.
Sir, you were right! We made it back
home, just like you said.
- It's a fortress!
- It's Lady Eboshi's Iron Town.
We make iron here
from the ore in the sand.
Hey, there! Hello! It's me!
- Someone's come out of the woods!
- Is it the wolf-girl?
Look! It's me, Kohroku, the ox driver!
It's true, Kohroku is still alive!
He can't be!
Quiet! Stop that noise! I'm trying to
tally these accounts, so shut up!
Haven't you heard?
Kohroku has come back from the dead!
What?
- This is unbelievable!
- Where are the others?
There were two others who fell there.
I'm afraid we're the only ones
who made it.
It's never the gods that die.
Stand aside.
That man in the weird costume, sir,
who do you think he could be?
He's obviously an outsider.
Listen to me!
This stranger saved our lives!
He carried the rifleman
all the way back here.
You should be grateful to him!
Hey, watch the arm!
Hold it right there!
I'm very grateful to you for bringing
these men back to us, stranger.
But something doesn't smell right.
You got back here almost as fast as we
did, and through the forbidden forest!
On top of that, you did it with
two badly injured men
and you want me to believe...
Kohroku! You're alive!
Toki, my love!
That's just great.
How are you gonna drive the ox now,
all banged up and mangled?
- But, my little flower...
- You scared me half to death!
Don't you "little flower" me!
I wish the wolves had eaten you.
Then maybe I could have found
a real husband!
Sweetness, can we discuss this later?
Toki, save your sweet nothings
for some other time!
As for you, Gonza, a fine captain of
the guard you are,
strutting and throwing your weight
around once the danger is over!
You never do a lick
of work around here.
That's unfair and untrue.
Thanks, stranger.
My husband is an idiot but I'm glad
he's safe and sound.
That's a relief. I was starting to think
I'd done something wrong by bringing
him back home.
Say, why don't you take the mask off,
I bet you're really handsome.
Gonza!
Bring the stranger to me later.
I would like to thank him personally.
Kohroku.
- Yes?
- I'm happy you're back and I apologize.
Okay.
Milady, you shouldn't
tell him things like that.
If you're too nice,
he will walk all over you.
I hope you'll forgive me too, Toki.
I was responsible,
I should never have let it happen.
That's all right, Milady,
if you hadn't been there
the wolves would have eaten everyone
and we'd have to find new husbands.
Get some rest, traveler.
I will see you this evening.
You're not handsome, you're gorgeous!
- Is he there?
- There he is!
Toki was right, he is handsome!
- Yeah, not bad.
- But he's so young!
That never stopped you before!
Quiet out there!
We lost some good men today!
There's lots of gorgeous men
in here, honey!
I've seen cattle that looked better.
Listen, stranger, why don't you
come over to our place?
You don't want to stay
in this stinky old barn.
We risked our lives to bring you
the rice you're all eating tonight.
So, watch your mouth.
And who made the iron
that paid for the rice?
We're pumping those bellows while you
pigs are in bed.
Actually, if it's not too much trouble,
I would like to see where you work.
- You would?
- We'll have to work in make-up tonight.
Don't be a stranger! Don't forget now,
we'll be waiting for you!
It's best not to pay them
any mind, you know.
Lady Eboshi spoils them rotten,
that's why they're like that.
They say that happy women
make a happy village.
Happy? These kind of women,
working here?
Women like that, it's a disgrace!
They defile the iron.
Lady Eboshi buys the contract of every
brothel girl she can find.
Milady has a kind heart, that's all.
You got rice on your chin, old man.
That's true! Everything here has turned
upside down since she showed up.
She's not even afraid of the gods,
that woman.
You should have seen
the way she dealt with Nago.
Who's Nago?
The gigantic boar-god.
He used to rule this whole forest.
We couldn't even get near
the mountains with him around.
Nothing to do but sit around,
staring at a bunch of angry boars.
See, the iron in the sand under this
town had all been dug out.
We tried to get at the iron
under the mountain
but Nago wasn't gonna stand for that.
But before we could get to the iron,
we had to clear away the forest.
And that's what made the boar angry.
He's feeling no pain!
One day, Lady Eboshi came along with
her warriors and their rifles.
Young man, what's wrong?
Is something hurting your arm?
No.
I was just thinking about the boar-god.
I was thinking how he must have died
filled with hate.
Forgive me for keeping
you waiting, stranger.
That's good iron.
We were running behind with
tomorrow's shipment.
Let's have a rest.
You may tell the others.
Yes, ma'am.
Some think you're a spy for the wolf-girl
or for Lord Asano and his samurai.
There are a lot of people out there
with their eyes on this iron.
Why are you here,
if you don't mind my asking?
I believe you'll recognize this.
It shattered the bones of a giant boar,
rotted his flesh and turned him
into a monster.
I fought with him, and for that I was
cursed with this mark on my arm.
And soon, it will kill me.
Where is it you come from?
I've never seen a red elk
like that before.
I have come a very long way.
I can't tell you more than that.
Answer Milady's question
or I'll cut you in half!
What do you plan to do?
What exactly are you here for?
To see with eyes unclouded by hate.
Eyes unclouded?
That explains it.
Come, I'll show you all my secrets.
Is that wise, Milady?
Gonza, take over for me.
This is my garden. None of the
townspeople dare to come here.
Follow me if you wish
to learn my secret.
Good evening.
We've only just finished it, Milady.
It's still too heavy.
Perhaps if you didn't
hold it so delicately?
Milady, if we make them any lighter,
they'll fall apart.
They're not for me,
they're for the other women here.
That will be something to see!
This is the latest rifle
that I've asked these people to design.
The ones we brought here
turned out to be too heavy.
These will kill forest monsters and
pierce the thickest samurai armor.
You'd better watch out there,
young man.
Lady Eboshi wants to rule the world!
I'm sorry to have to push you all so
hard. I'll have wine sent down later.
That would be nice!
First you steal the boar's forest from
him, then transform him into a demon.
Now you make even deadlier weapons.
How much hate and pain do we need?
Yes. I'm the one who shot the boar.
I'm sorry that you suffer. I truly am.
That brainless pig! I'm the one he
should have put a curse on, not you!
Does that right hand of yours wish to
kill me now, Ashitaka?
If it would lift the curse,
I'd let it tear you apart.
But even that wouldn't end the killing
now, would it?
No, it wouldn't. You would have to
kill all of us to be at peace.
Milady, Osa has something to say.
Forgive me, Milady, but you must not
make light of the boy's strength.
Young man, like you,
I know what rage feels like,
and grief, and helplessness.
But you must not take your revenge
on Lady Eboshi.
She's the only one who saw
us as human beings.
We are lepers.
The world hates and fears us,
but she took us in and washed our
rotting flesh and bandaged us...
Osa.
Life is suffering. It is hard.
The world is cursed.
But still, you find reasons to keep living.
I'm sorry. I'm making no sense.
They just keep coming back.
Every night they're out there
planting trees.
Trying to turn the mountain
into a forest again.
Stay here. Help me
kill the forest spirit, Ashitaka.
You would do that?
Kill the very heart of the forest?
Without that ancient god,
the animals here would be nothing
but dumb beasts.
When the forest has been cleared
and the wolves wiped out,
this desolate place
will be the richest land in the world.
And Princess Mononoke will become
human.
Princess Mononoke?
Princess of the spirits of ghouls,
beasts and ancient gods.
The wolves stole her soul
and now she lives to kill me.
The legends say the blood of the great
forest spirit can heal anything.
Perhaps it could cure my poor lepers.
It might even be able to lift your curse.
Milady?
- How does the action feel to you?
- Better.
Smooth as silk.
The perfect thing for ruling the world.
But still too heavy for the girls.
All right.
Well, look who's here.
Evening.
All right if I work the bellows for a while?
I guess so.
Excuse me. May I try it?
It's okay. Might as well let him try.
I can't believe he came here.
Yeah. What a catch, huh?
That guy really cares about us!
I'm impressed.
But you'll never keep that pace up.
It's hard work, isn't it?
You bet.
And our shifts are four days long.
You must lead hard lives here.
I suppose. But it sure beats working a
brothel in the city, huh?
Here we get to eat as much as we want,
and the men don't bother us.
No! You can't leave tomorrow!
- Couldn't you stay a little longer?
- You can stay and work here!
Thank you all, but there's someone
I have to find out there in the forest.
She's here.
The wolves are coming!
It's the wolf-princess!
Hurry!
Stop!
I don't want to fight you. I'm a friend!
She's over here!
Hurry! She's after Lady Eboshi!
Keep stoking those fires!
Riflemen to the stockade!
We've got her right where we want her.
A weapon for every man!
Everyone defends Iron Town!
Toki, she's on the roof!
Now don't get excited.
Keep those bellows working.
Whatever happens,
we can't let those fires go out.
- Is she alone?
- Yes.
She can't escape,
we have her cornered.
We know she means
to kill you this time.
We'll see about that. Come on!
Can you hear me, princess of beasts?
If it's me you want, here I am.
If you seek revenge for all the animals
we've Killed,
there are two women down here
I'd like you to meet.
They want revenge as well,
for husbands killed by your wolves.
Come on out, you little witch!
My husband is dead because of you.
Everybody out of the way!
Riflemen, get ready to fire!
It's a trap. No, wait!
Princess of the wolf-gods, don't go
down there! Go back to the forest!
Listen to me, please,
don't throw your life away!
Shall I stop him?
Leave him be. Let him do as he likes.
She's down! We got her!
Stay back.
Cut off a wolf's head and he still has
the power to bite.
What?
Take aim where she falls.
Open fire!
No! Stay back!
Wake up!
No!
Kill her, Milady!
Are you all right? Can I help you?
- Get away from me! Be gone!
- Yes, Sir.
Traitor!
You're a spy for the wolves, aren't you?
Stay back!
Step aside.
What do you think you're doing, boy?
Stay your hand,
the girl's life is now mine.
I'm sure she'll make
a lovely wife for you.
There is a demon inside of you.
It's inside both of you.
Look, everyone!
This is what hatred looks like.
This is what it does when it catches
hold of you.
It's eating me alive.
Very soon, it will kill me.
I'm getting a little bored of this
curse of yours, Ashitaka.
Let me just cut the damn thing off!
Milady!
Someone come here
and take her from me.
Milady!
Don't worry, she's just stunned.
She'll be all right.
As for me, I'm leaving.
And I'm taking the wolf-girl.
No, you're not!
Nobody treats Lady Eboshi like that.
Move and I fire!
Kiyo, what are you doing?
How can he still be walking?
- Is she all right?
- Yes, Milady is safe, sir.
Someone bring me my gun! Riflemen
to the square, now, on the double!
They're not getting out of here alive.
Toki, come here!
What's happened?
Sir, I can't let you pass.
The gate's been ordered shut.
It can't be opened!
Turn back, please!
We're grateful to you for bringing
those men back to us.
- We don't want to hurt you.
- Please!
I walked in through this gate
this morning.
Now I'm going to leave the same way.
Don't be a fool.
It takes ten men to open this gate.
Stop it! You'll kill yourself.
Out of the way!
The wolves are attacking!
Flint!
Stop! She's all right.
Your princess is safe with me.
Stay and I will bring her.
Come on, Yakul.
You have my thanks.
Good luck, stranger.
Stop it!
Leave him, he's mine!
His own people shot him.
He's dying.
Why did you stop me from killing her?
Tell me while you're still alive!
I did not want to let you die.
I'm not afraid of death. If I want to
drive away humans, I don't need my life.
I knew it from the very first time we met.
You're bothering me
and dying for nothing!
I'll cut your throat for you so I don't
have to listen to any more of this.
Live.
That's enough!
I'm not listening to you anymore.
You're beautiful.
What is it, San?
Want me to crunch his face off?
The ape tribe.
All right, what do you want here?
Apes! How dare you show such
disrespect to the wolf clan!
This is our forest.
The human, give him to us.
Give us the human and go.
You go, before my fangs find you.
We will not go.
We will eat the human.
Yes, let us eat the man-creature.
Are you crazy? What happened to make
the ape tribe change this way?
Since when do apes
eat the flesh of a man?
If we eat the human
we will steal his strength
and we will drive
the other humans away.
Give us the man-creature.
Stop this! You know you can't possess
the humans' strength by eating them.
All that will do is make you
into something else.
Something even worse than human.
We plant trees. Humans tear them up.
The forest does not come back.
If we kill the humans,
we will save the forest.
You mustn't give up. He'll find a way.
The forest spirit is with us.
Go on planting your trees and
someday we'll beat them.
The forest spirit will not fight.
We will all die.
Wolf-girl does not care. She is human.
Enough! I'll bite your head off,
you chattering ape!
Stop! Come back!
Leave them alone!
Don't worry about them. It's all right.
You go on ahead now.
I'll stay here and deal with the human.
What about the elk? Can we eat him?
No, you may not. Go home!
Come over here!
Don't worry, I'm a friend.
Don't be shy, now. I won't hurt you.
I need you to help me carry him.
You are very wise. You know better
than to set foot on this island.
I smell like a human.
You can go wherever you want to.
You're free now.
Finally!
There he is! Come and see. Hurry!
Quick, you idiots! It's the Nightwalker.
He's the reason we've been sitting
around in these stinking animal skins.
But sir, we can't. It's a sin to look at it.
And you call yourself the greatest
hunter in the west!
Look, we've got a letter of pardon
from the Emperor
forgiving us for cutting off the
head of the great forest spirit.
The legends tell us
that when day becomes night,
the forest spirit
turns into the Nightwalker.
And at sunrise, it changes back.
Look! See there? It's happening.
- Take a look. Master Jigo.
- What is it?
Over there.
Look! There must be hundreds of them.
These boars are not from this region.
They must have been traveling for
months to get all the way up here.
That one is Okkoto!
It can't be!
They say he died a hundred years ago.
It's him all right! I know those old tusks!
And it looks like he brought along
his whole tribe.
He's seen us, let's get out of here.
Come on, you cowards! Move, quickly!
The bullet wound is gone!
Yakul!
Finally, you're awake.
You really should thank Yakul.
He hasn't left your side this whole time.
How do you know his name is Yakul?
He told me. And he told me about you.
About your village,
your people and your forest.
The forest spirit brought you back
to life again. He wants you to live.
I had the strangest dream.
There was a golden creature.
Eat this.
Chew.
We're here to kill the humans
and save the forest.
Why are there humans here, Moro?
The girl is San, my daughter.
Humans are everywhere these days.
Go back to your own mountain.
Kill them there.
We will kill them here!
We will save this forest.
What is that other human doing here?
He was shot. And then the great spirit
healed his wound.
This man is not our enemy.
The forest spirit saved him?
Saved the life of that loathsome runt?
Why didn't he save Nago?
Is he not the guardian of the forest?
Why?
The forest spirit gives life and takes
life away.
Life and death are his alone.
Or have you boars forgotten that?
You lie! You must have begged the
forest spirit to save his life.
But you didn't beg for Nago, did you?
Nago was afraid to die.
Now I, too, carry within my breast
a poisoned human bullet.
Nago fled, and the darkness took him.
I remain and contemplate my death.
Mother, please ask the
forest spirit to save you.
I have lived long enough, San.
Soon the forest spirit
will let me rest forever.
All these years you've defended the
forest spirit. He must save you.
You are not fooling us!
Nago was beautiful and strong.
He would not have run from anything!
You wolves must have eaten him.
Quiet!
Watch what you say, you filthy pig!
Gods of the mountain,
please listen to me.
Nago died far from here,
and I was the one who killed him.
He had become some kind of demon.
One day, he attacked our village.
If you want proof, look at my hand
where he touched me.
I came here to beg the forest spirit to
lift Nago's curse from me.
He healed the bullet wound in my side,
but the demon mark remains.
First it will tear my soul apart,
and then it will kill me.
Okkoto.
Finally, a boar who will listen to reason.
No, Lord Okkoto, wait!
Please, you mustn't eat him.
You are Moro's human child,
aren't you?
I've heard of you.
You're blind!
Stand back. I will not eat him.
It's all right, San.
Lord Okkoto, what I said about
Nago's death was the truth.
I believe you, and I thank you for it,
young one.
I'm only grieved and ashamed that such
a demon has come from our tribe.
Oh mighty Lord, is there a way to lift
Nago's curse from me?
Leave this forest, or the next time
we meet, I'll have to kill you.
You cannot win against the humans.
Their guns will destroy you all.
Look on my tribe, Moro.
We grow small, and we grow stupid.
We will soon be nothing
but squealing game
that the humans hunt for their meat.
You'd risk everything on one last battle?
That's just what the humans want.
I do not ask for the help of the wolf tribe.
Even if every one of us dies,
it will be a battle
the humans will never forget.
The forest spirit!
Come on. Keep your oxen together.
Hurry!
Get ready now. A little bit closer...
Fire!
My arm!
Reload. Fire!
Attack!
Ready?
I see somebody is going to have to go
play the peacemaker.
Take our riflemen
and hide behind the cliffs.
There they are,
coming around the pass!
The hunters are ready, sir.
Excellent. Well done, my boy.
Go and spread the word.
We'll be moving out presently.
Yes, sir.
Greetings, Jigo.
Well, I've got the Emperor breathing
down my neck
and you're busy playing war
with Lord Asano.
And you would have nothing to do with
Lord Asano being here now, would you?
Of course not.
Whatever made you think that?
He'll call a truce
If 1 give him half my iron.
Is that right? He's a greedy bastard,
isn't he?
But all the same, you might as well let
him have his iron.
The boars are gathering for battle,
and you know what that means.
You made me a promise.
Once you get me the head of the forest
spirit,
we can come back and destroy
Lord Asano together.
Watch out, Milady, there are some
horsemen coming, get in!
Speak of the devil.
A messenger from Lord Asano.
We have guests.
Mind your manners, ladies.
We will.
Welcome back, Milady!
Wait, won't you even talk to the man?
Lady Eboshi, mistress of Iron Town.
I bring a message to you
from my Lord Asano.
You have fought valiantly and well.
Now open your gates,
that we may speak with you.
We can hear you just fine
from down there!
Milady took this mountain away from
the gods, the boars and the beasts!
And now that it's worth something,
you want it!
- You won't get it!
- The brazen impudence!
You ladies need to be
taught some respect.
"Respect"? What's that?
We haven't had any respect since
the day we were born!
You want some of our iron?
Here you go!
They are really something!
They'll fight forest gods or samurai,
it doesn't matter to them.
They're an amazing bunch, your girls.
They were wasted in the brothels.
Impressive for a piece of paper.
It's gotten me all the best hunters
and trappers around.
Remember, my dear lady, we're after a
god, not just a beast.
Yes, Milady, what is it?
Do you have any idea
who this paper has come from?
From the Emperor himself.
- The Emperor?
- Did you say the "Emperor"?
- His Imperial Majesty.
- His Imperial Majesty?
Yes, they're really something.
- Thank you.
- Yes, Milady.
Every day that we cut trees
and dig for iron,
the forest and its creatures
grow weaker.
My way. There is no loss of life, Jigo.
Listen, you owe me
and I've come to collect.
When you needed riflemen, I sent them.
And without those riflemen,
you lose Iron Town.
I'm sorry, did that sound like a threat?
Don't tell me the Emperor
believes that old wives' tale
about the great spirit's head
granting immortality.
I'm sure I don't know
what the Emperor believes.
I'm just a humble monk.
I'm just trying to get by.
I keep my promises.
Anyway, we have fought
the boars before.
They are much easier to kill than Moro
and her wolf cubs.
You can call out that shady bunch
you've got hidden under the cliff.
So, I've been found out!
Just one more thing, Milady.
Did a stranger come through here,
by any chance?
He's a young man riding
a great big red elk.
Came and went.
A bad-looking bunch, if you ask me.
Those men are no ordinary hunters.
They're Killers.
Killers?
Milady, at least let some of us go
with you!
You can't trust these men,
they're strangers!
What if something goes wrong and
we're stuck here? We can't help you!
You said yourself we're better shots
than the men are.
That's precisely why I want you all
here in Iron Town.
I can deal with forest gods.
It's humans I'm worried about.
Once the forest spirit is dead,
we don't know what will happen.
Will Jigo be satisfied
with the creature's head
or will he be after
my ironworks as well?
Jigo's riflemen might turn on us.
If that happens, I'll need every one of
you here to fight them.
Remember, you can't trust men.
Don't worry about Her Ladyship.
I'll be right at her side, protecting her.
- That's what we're afraid of.
- What?
Even if you were a woman,
you'd still be an idiot.
In the moonlight I felt your heart
Quiver like a bowstring's pulse
In the moon's pale light
You looked at me
Nobody knows your heart
When the sun has gone I see you
Beautiful and haunting, but cold
Like a knife in the dark
That cuts so deep
Nobody knows your heart
All of your sorrow, grief and pain
Locked away in the forests of the night
Your secret heart belongs to the ghosts
And the things that cry in the dark
Is it too hard?
You know, you could always jump, boy.
End it all.
As soon as your strength returns,
the mark will spread and destroy you.
It feels like I must have been
asleep for weeks.
I had a dream that San was
by my side, nursing me.
I was hoping you'd cry out
in your sleep.
Then I would have bitten your head off
to silence you.
It's a beautiful forest.
Are Okkoto and the boars
on the move yet?
Yes, the boars are marching.
The trees cry out as they die,
but you cannot hear them.
I live here.
I listen to the pain of the forest
and feel the ache
of the bullet in my chest.
And I dream of the day
when I will finally
crunch that gunwoman's head
in my jaws.
Moro, why can't the humans and the
forest live together?
Why can't we stop this fighting now?
The humans are gathering
for the final battle.
The flames of their guns will burn us all.
And what happens to San? What's
your plan, to let her die with you?
Typical. Selfish.
You think like a human.
San is my daughter.
She is of the wolf tribe.
When the forest dies, so does she.
You must set her free!
She's not a wolf, she's human.
Silence, boy!
How dare you speak to a god like that?
I caught her human parents
defiling my forest.
They threw their baby at my feet
as they ran away.
Instead of eating her,
I raised her as my own.
Now my poor, ugly, beautiful daughter
is neither human, nor wolf.
How could you help her?
I don't know.
But at least we might find a way to live.
How? Will you join forces with San
and fight the humans?
No. All that would do
IS cause more hatred.
There is nothing you can do, boy.
Soon the demon mark will spread
and Kill you.
Now leave this place at sunrise.
You're feeling all right?
I'm fine, thanks to you
and the forest spirit.
Right.
Yakul, sorry if I worried you.
I guess my legs are still pretty weak.
It's so quiet. I wonder where our
friends the little Kodama went.
I can smell the ironworks.
Thanks for showing us the way!
I have another favor to ask.
Will you please give this to San for me?
Let's go.
It stinks!
I think my nose is going to fall off.
That's what they want.
They're trying to kill our sense of smell.
It's that damn woman again.
She knows we're out here.
It's a trap, and a stupid one.
What?
They're trying to lure the boars
out of the forest.
The humans are planning something.
Then we have to find Okkoto while
there's still time to stop him!
Or else, they'll all be killed!
Okkoto is too stubborn. He won't listen.
None of them will.
They may even know it's a trap.
The boars are a proud race.
The last one left alive
will still be charging blindly forward.
Why chop the trees down?
To make them angry,
which makes them stupid.
Mother, I have to go.
Okkoto is blind, I must be his eyes.
You understand?
Do as you must.
You know, that boy wanted to share his
life with you.
I hate all humans.
From Ashitaka? For me?
Pretty.
You two, stay with San.
I must go to the forest spirit.
Right. Let's go.
The Moro tribe has come
to fight with you.
Where can I find Lord Okkoto?
Good luck, my friend!
It's coming from Iron Town.
Let's go!
Halt! Who goes there?
Samurai again!
Halt, I said!
Out of the way!
What the devil was that?
He stopped it!
Great!
Don't waste your arrows. Cease fire!
Toki, come and look!
It can't be. It's Ashitakal
So it's not a ghost.
- Ashitaka!
- Tokil!
Are you all right?
We're all right.
Lord Asano and his samurai thought
they'd try and ambush us
while our men were away.
Thought we'd just roll over.
But we showed them!
Where's Lady Eboshi?
She took every able-bodied man
and went to kill the forest spirit.
We're cut off here, we can't even get a
message to Lady Eboshi.
The forest spirit!
That explains the explosions.
Sir, I've still got your bow and arrows.
Aren't you gonna tell him you've got
his cloak and saddle, too?
- I do?
- You're useless!
Many thanks, Kohroku!
I'll try and bring you some help.
Can you hold out?
Don't worry.
We can always pour hot iron on them.
- Bring back Lady Eboshi!
- And don't take too long!
I missed.
They're bringing boats across the river.
Go and get Lady Eboshi.
We'll hold them off as long as we can!
I'll be back, I promise!
We'll be here!
Get him! Stop that man!
Looks like they're gonna try
to cut us off. Run, Yakul!
Burning animal flesh.
Yakul!
Stay back!
Show me your wound.
You'll have to stay here. Wait for me.
I'll come back for you.
I said, stay!
We're almost there, my friend.
Who goes there?
My orders are,
no outsiders permitted here.
All right, but I just
came from Iron Town.
I have a message for Lady Eboshi.
Tell me where I can find her.
The Eboshi woman is not here.
Give me the message,
I'll make sure she gets it.
I must speak with her.
Now, where is she?
It's really you?
You're still alive, lad?
It looks like you men
had a worse time than I did.
We've been burying our friends all day.
It was horrible!
Iron Town has come under attack.
What?
The women and the lepers have fallen
back to the inner wall.
We haven't got a lot of time.
Those samurai bastards!
Asano must have just been waiting for
us to leave Iron Town.
Now I must find Lady Eboshi.
She's off hunting down the forest spirit.
Then someone has to stop her.
Call her back!
If you're all done, I want you out of here.
The rest of you, keep digging!
- Wait! What about Iron Town?
- That's right! It's our home!
What do they expect us to do,
just abandon Iron Town?
You heard the boy,
we haven't a moment to lose!
Send a message to Lady Eboshi!
The forest is too big. No messenger
would have a chance of finding her.
One of your hunters could find her!
What else are they good for?
Lady Eboshi is just being used by Jigo.
When you fought with the boars,
were there any wolves with them?
Did you see San, the wolf-girl?
I have no idea. It was pitch black
when the animals came at us.
She was there. I saw her.
I was right in the front line,
I saw everything!
What happened?
I'm not sure. Everything started
happening so fast! It was a nightmare!
Jigo's troops put us in front as bait
to lure the boars in.
They didn't tell us about live landmines
under our feet
or the grenades coming in on top of us.
Where is she? Where's San?
Take it easy, I'm trying to get you out!
There's a wolf over there. Hurry!
Young master, what are you doing?
- What's going on?
- Move!
What do you think you're doing?
I've got to find Lady Eboshi.
This wolf is gonna help me find her.
You're on their side, aren't you, boy?
Stand aside!
What's more important to all of you?
The head of the forest spirit,
or saving your town?
Those darts are poison!
That's enough now!
Come on, let's get this thing off of
them, all together now!
Look out!
After you've come through the swamp,
take cover by the lake
until we get there.
Right!
Be careful. Those riflemen
with Milady belong to Jigo.
Take these. Where I'm going,
they won't be of any use.
You go with them, Yakul.
Look after him.
Find San!
That's where we'll find Eboshi.
Come on, keep moving, straight ahead.
Today, we finish this.
Sir.
Have you spotted them?
Okkoto is badly wounded,
but he and the wolf-girl
are making their way to the realm of
the forest spirit.
So, they're going to beg him
for his help, are they?
Keep after them.
But stay out of sight, or you'll
frighten the forest spirit away.
Yes, sir. I understand.
That was boar's blood painted on his
face, wasn't it?
A little trade secret.
Don't want to smell human.
We're almost to the pool.
Just a little farther, keep going.
What was that?
Okkoto, there's something wrong!
We have to keep moving.
Something is out there.
But what? There's so much blood
in the air, I can't smell it.
I should have known it was you!
You did this!
Because of you, the forest will die!
You're wrong!
We've both been fighting to save it.
This is the thanks you give us?
You bring bad things.
Bad things coming,
neither human nor animal.
What do you mean,
neither human nor animal?
- They're coming!
- It's the end for us.
They're warriors.
They've come back.
My warriors!
They have come back to me
from the land of the dead.
Forward, my warriors!
Forward to the pool of the forest spirit!
No, Lord Okkoto, your warriors
haven't come back to you!
Those are humans wearing the skins of
your warriors to hide their scent!
It's a trick!
Don't you understand?
It's just a human trick
to get us to lead them
to the forest spirit.
Come out, forest spirit!
If you are truly master here,
give my warriors the power to slay
the humans and be victorious!
Stop, Lord Okkoto, please!
You've got to listen.
San, they're all around us.
Okkoto's done for, leave him!
No! I won't let him turn into a demon,
like Nago did.
Tell Mother that the humans are setting
a trap for the forest spirit.
She'll know what to do.
You'll have to hurry, or it could mean
the end of all of us!
Go on now.
Stay back or you die!
And then this whole forest will see
just what you are.
Ashitaka?
I burn.
There are flames growing inside of me!
You must fight it!
Don't let yourself become a demon.
Lord Okkoto!
What is it?
Is it San?
- She's in danger.
- Let's go!
Fire!
No! I don't want to become a demon.
Please, stop, Okkoto!
You're too slow. Get on!
A wolf!
Eboshi!
You keep going!
Eboshi! I have something to say!
Hold your fire!
What is it you want?
Lord Asano's samurai have attacked
Iron Town!
The women are outnumbered,
they can't hold them up for long!
Forget about the forest spirit.
Your men are already
back to Iron Town
but they need you to lead them.
What proof is there this isn't a lie?
Lie? Don't be ridiculous.
What reason do I have to lie?
So it's, "Don't kill the forest gods?"
Now you want us
to kill samurai instead?
No! What I want is for the humans and
the forest to live in peace.
Whose side is he on anyway?
Shouldn't we go back?
The women are on their own now.
I've done all I can for them.
They can take care of themselves.
There's the pool Kohroku told us about.
The creature must be
somewhere nearby.
It's the moment of truth, boys.
So keep your eyes peeled.
Why do we need that woman, sir?
When you're going to kill a god,
let someone else do the dirty work.
Moro, what happened to you?
San! It's me, Ashitaka!
San!
Ashitaka!
Okkoto! Turned into a demon!
Leave, boy.
Fight me,
and the forest spirit will never come.
Lord Okkoto, calm your fury!
Oh mighty Lord, let me have the girl,
I beg of you.
Please, let her go.
San, are you there?
It's me, Ashitaka!
San!
Let's put him down!
Stop him, he'll ruin everything!
San!
Ashitaka!
Here I was,
saving the last of my strength
to bite off that damn woman's head.
But I must save San.
Close ranks! Use your grenades!
Don't touch him. He's no longer a god.
You can't even speak, can you?
Well done, man. Now fall back and get
the wounded out of here.
Go on.
What a revolting spectacle.
It's him.
Give me back my daughter, demon!
Ashitaka.
Can you save the girl you love?
The forest spirit!
Eboshi, hold your fire!
Eboshi!
Your enemy is not the forest spirit.
But that should have killed it!
He's a god,
it will take more than one shot.
San!
Don't die!
I don't get it! The great forest
spirit took their lives away.
Quick! He's starting to change.
Now watch closely, everyone.
I'm going to show you how to kill a god.
A god of life and death.
The trick is not to fear him.
No, stop!
Eboshi!
You will die!
She did it! Quickly, go get the head!
Quick, Jigo! Bring me that box of yours.
The porters are all dead.
Hurry, hurry!
Be careful not to touch the spirit's body.
It will suck the life out of you!
Here it is. One head, as promised!
Watch out!
Milady!
I told you a wolf's head can still bite.
Come on!
We've got to get out of here. Hurry!
It's coming, sir!
Run!
Gonza, we've got to get to the island!
Island? I can't swim!
Then walk along the bottom.
Give her to me. I'll cut her throat!
Your clan has been avenged.
Your mother saw to that.
- Lady Eboshi!
- Help me.
Don't waste your sympathy.
I promised Toki that I'd bring you back
to Iron Town.
He's searching for his head.
We can't stay here.
San! You have got to help us.
No!
You're on their side, you always were!
Take that damned woman
and just go away!
San.
Never! I hate all of you, humans!
Yes, I'm human, San. But so are you.
Stop it! I'm a wolf, you hear?
- San.
- Stay back!
I'm sorry. I tried to stop it.
It's over. Everything is over.
The forest is dead.
Nothing is over.
The two of us are still alive.
Now, will you help me, San?
Help us! Come back!
A little crisis and they panic.
What are you doing? This way!
Look! The head is moving.
It's calling him to us!
There you go, Toki.
Thanks.
It's awfully quiet.
Asano is waiting for sunrise.
I wonder if that young man
ever found Lady Eboshi.
Don't worry about him,
he found her all right!
They'll be marching
over that hill any minute now.
Big dope! Don't ask me why I love him.
Hey, Kohroku!
Let him sleep, Toki. While he can.
What's that?
I don't like it.
It's the Nightwalker!
Everybody, hold your positions!
- It's coming right at us!
- Run! We gotta go!
No! We promised Lady Eboshi
we would defend Iron Town.
Look, over there! He's come back!
Get everyone out!
The great spirit's head has been cut
off, and he wants it back!
If that black ooze touches you,
you're dead!
Run for the lake,
the water will slow it down.
Lady Eboshi and the men are on their
way from the other side.
I'm going to try to return his head
before he kills us all.
Hurry!
It's too fast!
It will kill us all!
That's enough!
Get everyone down to the lake
and stay calm.
We can carry the sick and the wounded.
Not that way! Stop!
There it goes.
We're done for.
Once the forge burns, that's it.
That will be the end of Iron Town.
We're still alive, Kohroku.
We'll manage somehow. Now let's go!
There they are!
Go!
Stop right there.
You're both alive. How nice.
I'm giving the creature back its head.
Put the box down and back away.
Give the head back now?
Come on, boy, don't be silly.
Now, when the sun is
about to come up?
Look, he's a brainless, swollen,
life-sucking god of death.
But at sunrise,
he'll vanish like a bad dream.
Sir, it's coming.
We've got to get out of here!
Look, everybody wants everything.
That's the way the world is.
But I might actually get it.
Don't force me to kill you.
You make it sound so very easy.
You really ought to
relax!
Get going!
Ashitaka!
I got it!
This is bad.
Master, we're surrounded!
- Come on, sun! Rise!
- Open the box!
Don't you see? It's too late for that now.
Why are you wasting
your breath talking to him?
Human hands must return it.
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Forest spirit!
I give you back your head!
Take it, and be at peace!
Well, that got its attention all right.
I think it's over.
Look, it's the men!
I can't believe we made it! I never
thought I'd live to see home again.
Milady!
Be careful,
Her Ladyship has been injured.
Look! It's falling on Iron Town.
Hang on tight, everybody! Don't let go!
I didn't know the forest spirit made
the flowers grow.
San! Look!
Even if all the trees return,
it won't be his forest anymore.
The great forest spirit is dead now.
Never. He's life itself.
He's not dead. He's here right now,
trying to tell us something.
That it's time for both of us to live.
Ashitaka, you mean so much to me.
But I can't forgive the humans
for what they've done.
I understand.
You'll live in the forest,
and I'll go help them rebuild Iron Town.
I'll always be near.
Yakul and I will come and visit you
whenever we can, all right?
Amazing. The wolves and that crazy
little wolf-girl helped save us all.
Ashitaka! Can someone find him?
I need to thank him.
We're going to start all over again.
This time, we'll build a better town.
Well, I give up.
You can't win against fools.