All right, everyone! Are you ready?
Who's our next quiz king? Do you wanna know?
Yeah!
Then let's get started with the prelim round!
You with me?
Yeah!
Quiz... trial... 7!
Question number one!
Here we go: "The term "adamant" refers to a diamond,
while the term "beryl" refers to an emerald."
So is this true, or is it false?
Not a terrible first question, I guess.
The answer is...
...it's true!
Time to show off my database skills.
Let's do this.
There aren't very many contestants left now.
Will question 7 be the last of the prelim round?
Let's see!
The word "darui," or "listless",
derives from the English word "dull."
Is this true, or is it false?
What do you think?
Well, it makes sense that it would be, but I don't know.
What's your answer, Mayaka?
Huh?
Do you think it's true or false?
Maybe... it's true?
The answer is...
The suspense is killing me!
...false!
And that's it for the preliminaries!
Wa-hoo!
If you answered correctly, congratulations!
The championship round will be held right over here!
Come on up!
Yo!
Wow, man.
That's one serious hat you're rockin' there.
Who's he again?
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
You didn't even realize I was competing, did you?
I was pretty focused on the quiz.
Oh, I remember him!
So, Tani, how's the Go Club?
The Go Club.
I've got a funny story about that, actually.
Wanna hear it?
Fantastic!
Now, let's hear from our third finalist.
Yeah, I'm coming!
We should go.
Whoa!
Looks like there's a giant Saturn on his head!
Please tell us your name and class.
Hello, folks. Satoshi Fukube!
Ooh!
From the Classic Lit Club!
Wow!
We have a Classic Lit Club? Who knew?
Based on that outfit, your club must be wild, huh?
Yeah!
Sure! We are totally wild!
I mean really, we've done a
lot of awesome stuff this year.
You have?
Please, tell us more!
Well, we knew that we needed to create an anthology,
and we wanted to make the most of it.
Honestly, I think the results are pretty amazing.
We put everything into it!
Oh, yeah. We put everything into it, money-wise.
As a matter of fact, we uncovered a
long-buried secret about this very festival!
Please, tell us more!
We found the origin of the term "Kanyasai."
It is not just a simple abbreviation of
"Kamiyama High School Cultural Festival."
The Classic Lit Club...
...has found the truth!
What is the name's origin?
To find out...
...buy our anthology!
For the low price of 200 yen,
you can learn the 45-year-old secret
of Kami High's cultural festival.
Purchase your copy of Hyouka
now in the Earth Science Prep Room
on the 4th floor of the auxiliary building!
Pitch successful!
At this point, winning is just gravy.
I'm here, Oreki!
How'd it go?
I talked to Tanabe.
He said we could ask other clubs to
sell copies for us at their booths.
My first thought was to find Irisu and
ask if she would consider helping us out,
but I never quite made it there.
Yeah. I think I can see why.
What should we do now?
Satoshi's plug was pretty
effective. Maybe that'll do the trick.
Huh? A plug!
That's it!
I heard the Wall Newspaper Club
is putting out an extra edition!
I'll go ask them if they'll
cover the Classic Lit Club in it.
Always on the move.
Excuse me!
Hey, Chitanda. Need something?
Actually, yes. I could use your help.
Could you cover the Classic Lit Club in your extra?
Huh?
I'm confused.
What is it that you want, exactly?
A small favor.
The club's run into some trouble.
I was hoping you might write a promotional
article for us and publish it in the wall newspaper.
Oh. Uh...
I dunno.
The thing is, I'm not really in the club anymore.
Since it's my last year of school, I've retired.
All right, I'm sorry.
Well, then, is there a chance you could
introduce me to the people who are running it now?
Sure, I don't mind doing that,
but it may not do you any good.
The one-page extra is set to run in two hours.
So the layout is pretty much fixed at this point.
So it's impossible to add anything?
For today, anyway.
But they might have some room available if
you can wait until the afternoon on day 2.
That said, there are more than 50 clubs at Kanyasai,
and the paper gives priority to
those that deserve the most attention.
And I'm not sure your club makes the cut.
No offense, but all you're doing
is publishing an anthology, right?
Yes, but, there's important information in it.
Come on, every club thinks that what it does is important.
Tell you what: if you can come up with a story
that's actually going to capture people's interest,
I'll personally ask them to run it, okay?
Yes. I understand.
Well, thank you,
and I'm sorry for taking up so much of your time.
Remember, if you come up with an interesting story,
drop by again.
I may be able to help you out.
Eru?
Hi, Kaho!
Long time no see.
How is Uncle Jumonji doing,
after everything that happened?
He's doing fine now.
How about you, though? You look kinda stressed.
I guess so. I've got a lot going on.
Well, maybe I can help.
I'll tell your fortune if you want.
This is a pretty amazing setup you've got here.
A lot of options, too.
I think I'd like to try a tarot reading.
Oh. I'm sorry, I can't do that.
Really? But why not?
Eru... You like a good mystery, right?
What is that?
I'm running this all by myself, so I
have to leave the booth unattended sometimes.
I stepped out for a little bit, and when I came back,
the Wheel of Fortune card was missing from my Tarot deck.
And that card had been left in its place.
It says "Jumonji." I don't get it. Why
would your last name be written on here?
Good question. I wish I knew.
Have you been able to track
down the card that disappeared yet?
I think I'll get it back eventually.
This note was left here, too.
I don't think I've ever heard of a
thief who puts things back before.
Here. If you don't mind, there's
one more thing I'd like to show you.
A festival guidebook? Is there something special about it?
As far as I can tell, it's the same as all the others.
I found it here the same time I found that card.
When I noticed it, it was open to the last
page... the one with all the club comments on it.
This is so strange. What do you think it means?
I have no idea,
but as long as I get my Wheel of Fortune
back safely, I'm willing to let it go at that.
It's almost time to crown a winner!
So is everybody ready?
Shimizu and Goto both have 5 points.
Meanwhile... Tani and Fukube have 6 points,
and both of them seem eager to clinch the title.
Which of our four competitors will be the champion?
Before we find out, let's give them all a hand!
All right, on to the next question.
Get ready!
The formula to determine the surface area of a sphere...
...is 4 pi r squared.
Oho! Quick one!
I haven't even finished the
question yet! Are you sure about this?
I'm sure.
All right, then. Shimizu, what's your answer?
The answer is 4/3 pi r cubed.
Correct!
Hooray!
The formula used to determine the
surface area of a sphere is 4 pi r squared.
Now, please tell us the formula
used to determine its volume.
That formula is 4/3 pi r cubed.
Quite impressive! Shimizu now has 6 points.
Three contestants are a step away from winning!
It's almost too exciting to handle!
You hang in there, Goto!
All right. On to our next question.
Get ready!
Kami High School's student
council president's full name...
...is what, contestants?
Yes? What is your answer?
Muneyoshi Kugayama.
Seriously, can we just get on with it?
Correct!
Let's give it up for...
Oh, well. Good game.
Huh? Yeah.
It was a close one. For both of us.
You're right. Then I guess we're even.
Yep. Guess we are.
I never did finish telling you that story.
Some of our Go stones were stolen from our room.
Really?
You sure they were stolen and not just lost?
There was a strange note left in the Go stone bowl saying,
"We've taken some stones from the Go Club."
And it's not like we use all of
them, so they could easily take 10,
and nobody would notice they were missing.
But what's the point of stealing them in the first place?
I'd say they're probably using them to play Five-in-a-Row.
It sounds like some other club is messing with you.
Well... bye.
Not so fast, Fukube.
I can't just let this end in a tie.
Let's settle it for good. Where are you competing next?
I'm doing the cooking club tomorrow.
You're on!
The Cooking Club will decide who the true winner is.
Looking forward to it!
You're the winner!
What's his deal?
How does it feel?
I couldn't care less about competing against Tani.
I wonder if Hotaro is hard at work...
You open?
Oh, yeah. Sure, we're open.
I hear there are some cool
Kanyasai facts in your little book.
You mind if I look through it?
I do, actually.
They're cheap enough, okay? Please buy one.
We've got so many copies, its killing us.
I don't know if you realized,
man, but your fly's unzipped.
Huh? Oh, crap!
Aww...
The whole zipper's torn off.
What am I gonna do?
You can have this if you want. It might help.
Oh, hey!
Lucky you've got one of these hanging around.
You're a lifesaver.
I'll tell ya what.
Take this.
That's not a real gun, is it?
Of course not. It's a water gun.
I'm in the gardening club.
We've been roasting sweet potatoes.
These seemed like a cooler way
to put out fires than buckets.
In that case, shouldn't you probably hang onto this?
Nah, I'm good. That's just my sidearm.
This is my main weapon right here.
AK, baby.
"Baby"?
Well, later, man. Thanks for the help.
A Glock 17. Just what I always wanted.
I'm telling you... it's no use.
This collection was doomed from the start.
We're not exactly drawing a crowd.
We should start making up posters.
Maybe that way, we can at least get a few customers.
I know.
It's frustrating, but we all decided
that this is what we wanted to do.
Why is everybody looking at me?
I mean, 100 manga reviews?
It's not like this is classic
literature we're talking about, here.
Please, Kochi. Just stop.
I don't see why anyone would
bother to read reviews of manga.
It's a waste of time. Right?
I... um, I don't know.
There's probably no chance Fuku will believe me,
but I really was trying to behave myself.
What do you mean, "why would anyone bother?"
I'm confused.
The fact is, all manga is basically the same.
Are you serious?
Sure, I am.
One manga is just as good as another,
so reviewing them is totally pointless.
You don't think the writing matters?
No, I don't.
If that's true, how are people supposed
to decide which one they want to read?
This isn't rocket science, Ibara.
People read what they're into.
Just think about it: a sports fan will read
about sports, and a romantic will read about romance.
It's as simple as that.
You're saying that people will read about what interests
them, without caring whether or not it's any good.
Exactly!
Which is why I don't think
there's any point in writing reviews.
Everyone should just read what they like.
This is entertainment, not fine art.
All manga is basically the same?
I can't let that statement stand.
I'll prove her wrong.
Let me clarify.
To you, no manga stands out above the rest, meaning
there are no works that can be considered masterpieces.
There are masterpieces.
And how would you define them?
Well, there are series that go on for many years
without losing popularity, even gaining readers over time.
That makes them masterpieces.
I think you're wrong.
A masterpiece is a masterpiece from the beginning.
It doesn't become one.
I don't see how a manga can possibly deserve
that title until it's stood the test of time.
That's just ignorant!
Excuse me?
It's a matter of personal experience.
Tell me this... Have you ever read
something that really got to you?
That made you laugh or cry so much it hurt?
Wow, Ibara.
Aren't you a passionate one...
There's a big gap between the
skill and talent of different artists.
For example...
There was a manga sold at last year's cultural festival
that was titled A Corpse by Evening. Have you read it?
No, I haven't.
Okay, then I'll bring it in tomorrow.
And if reading that still doesn't convince you,
then nothing I could say ever would.
Nice.
That pretty much guarantees I won't
be able to leave copies of Hyouka here.
I'll take one, please.
Here you go. Thanks a lot.
Were they all listening?
Hi! Thanks for coming!
Battle of the Maidens? Sounds interesting.
Excuse me.
What's up?
What is that?
Sorry, it's over now.
They'll go at it again tomorrow, though.
So feel free to stop by then.
Sure.
So... What did you think?
About my plug, I mean.
Did it help our situation at all?
Yeah, I suppose.
We sold 14.
Yeah? That many?
Guess this means publicity really works.
It looks like we're off to a pretty good start.
I'll try to do it again tomorrow.
The cooking contest should give me a nice opportunity.
You mean the "three-person team" competition?
Huh?
It's a team competition?! Seriously?
Shouldn't someone on the executive
committee know these little details?
I struck out.
I didn't increase our number of outlets,
and I couldn't get the newspaper to do a story on us.
I'm sorry I failed.
Don't beat yourself up.
Although...
I did hear something that I'm kind of curious about.
Of course you did.
Never mind.
It's nothing. Just forget about it.
That's a great idea.
See?
It doesn't say anything about three-person teams!
I don't know what to tell ya.
I heard it straight from one
of the girls in the Cooking Club.
Aww... What am I gonna do?
I thought I could enter on my own.
What about you, Mayaka?
How did it go with the Manga Club?
Just fine, thank you very much.
Ladies... Can I ask a favor?
Would you please consider entering
the Cooking Club contest with me?
I can ask the Manga Club president if
she'll give me time away from our booth.
If it'll help with publicity, I'm definitely in.
Great!
If we work hard, I know we can win it!
It sounds like you're really invested in this.
Well, I am fairly proud of my cooking ability.
And honestly, I would hate to
pass up a chance to show it off.
Attention, all students and visitors.
We hope you had an excellent time.
This announcement marks the
end of our Kanyasai's first day,
and what a fantastic one it was!
Oreki, this envelope...
You didn't look, right?
Uh... No way.
Yeah. Of course. I was just checking.
Where is it?
Not here.
Where could it have gone?
I guess I'll bring this instead.
No! I'll find it!
I've looked everywhere.
Where is it?
Next time:
"Wild Fire."