So, Chitanda, can you say with certainty
that you will catch the phantom thief Jumoji?
Of course we will!
Well, that's our intention.
With all of your...
With everyone helping us out,
I don't think there's any logical reason
that we wouldn't be able to catch Jumoji!
Whoa, that's a pretty bold statement!
Then my next question: What do
you think Jumoji is after now?
Well, we've already gotten something
ready that fits his pattern of thefts:
proofed manuscripts.
Proofed manuscripts?
Yes.
Corrected drafts of the Classic
Lit Club's anthology, Hyouka.
Huh?
Are there fewer of them?
Our anthology contains a story no less compelling
than the Jumoji Caper, so come pick one up!
Because if you like mystery as much as we do,
you'll love this tale that will
keep you on the edge of your seat!
Wow, that does sound pretty intriguing!
Yes.
Everyone! Please come check out the
Classic Lit Club's anthology, Hyouka!
It's great! I know you're all gonna love it! Thanks!
One more thing,
as we're getting ready to roll out the red carpet
for Jumoji, we'd like to ask everyone for a small favor.
Oh, yeah? And what's that?
Well, since there are only four of us in the
club, we need help keeping an eye on everything.
So everyone, if you have some free
time, come help the Classic Lit Club!
And I mean everyone!
We are counting on all of you to help!
I understand!
Strength in numbers, am I right?
Yes!
We expect everyone to come help us out! Thanks in advance!
Hmm... I've always been a sucker for a desperate request!
Another thing...
...if you come by and you think you can...
...please buy an anthology. Okay?
And so, the final target, the Classic
Lit Club, is more than ready to engage!
Well, Chitanda, happy hunting!
Thank you for your time.
We hope you all decide to stand with us.
That was Eru Chitanda, everyone!
Okay, we're off the air.
Hey, that was a decent interview!
Thank you very much.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just not sure if I should be doing all of this.
One, please.
200 yen.
Whoa! They're selling! This is great!
We're so close. Almost sold out.
Do you think he's really coming?
As packed as this place is right now,
he couldn't make his move!
Yeah, you're right.
It'd be impossible like this.
How long do you think this thief is going to make us wait?
Does Jumoji even exist?
Could they be doing all of this themselves?
Yeah, I hadn't even thought of that!
Show yourself, already, Jumoji.
Sorry about that. Just my cell phone.
Geez.
You gonna answer?
Nah. Not till after our watch...
Hey, it's on fire!
It's on fire!
Put it out! Put it out!
Water?
We've been had.
Look. He left this.
It's Jumoji's confession note, all right.
I hate to say, "I told you so."
Wait, you never said this would happen!
He got them good, huh?
Now I'm thinking Jumoji might be a girl!
Huh? What makes you say that?
I mean, just think about it.
We sold out.
Huh?
I'm sorry I couldn't sell them at the list price.
No, don't worry! This is great!
Thanks so much. I mean it.
Really, you have no idea!
Oh, stand up. And another thing...
Yes?
I don't know if I should tell you this...
Should tell me what?
I heard your radio broadcast.
Oh, did you think that I followed your advice correctly?
Look, about that...
My advice was a bit too literal.
I want to be clear about this.
You aren't really suited for stuff like that.
When you try so hard to manipulate the expectations
of others, you come across as kind of needy.
Needy?
Do you really think that's how I sounded?
Maybe as much as the tip of my little finger.
However, sometimes, if you pretend to be something,
you wind up becoming that way in your real life somehow.
Right.
You'd really do better to not take my words at
face value if you're only going to botch the execution.
You might see your inability
to manipulate as a shortcoming,
but under the right circumstances,
it's a valuable weapon.
So... You understand?
Yes. I was kind of thinking the same thing!
I'm just not cut out for this sort of stuff.
I guess, what I mean is...
Well... I've had enough.
That was exciting.
Wow, not even the Classic Lit
Club could catch Jumoji, huh?
I expected so much from you.
Yeah, well...
Sorry I haven't lived up to your expectations.
No way.
It was still an entertaining cultural festival.
Plus, I got my revenge for the cooking competition.
See ya.
Who's he?
That's Tani.
He doesn't get the subtleties of language.
You know?
What do you mean?
He said "expected."
That's not really what you say to
your opponent when neither of you won.
Why does that matter? "Expected"...
Using that word implies that it's finished.
If you still believe in yourself, it's not appropriate.
The way he phrased it...
It's not right, 'cause this isn't over.
Unless there's no hope, and things have gone worse
than imagined, there's no point in using that word.
Fukube...
Anyway, the cards haven't all fallen.
I swear I saw Hotaro come this way.
There he is.
Let's cut to the chase, then, shall we?
You are Jumoji, aren't you?
You might as well confess.
What? Just a shot in the dark?
Tanabe's Jumoji?
First, there's your card.
Why does it always say "lost,"
rather than "stolen" or "taken?"
Who knows?
My next question deals with the
letter "ku." Why did you skip it?
That alone should eliminate the Jumoji theory,
but what if it dealt with some element that
the rest of the school didn't know anything about?
Something not meant for the public.
Oh? Like what?
The Jumoji Caper itself.
The entire affair was only a code, wasn't it?
You had to deliver a message,
to one whose name starts with "ku,"
and something beginning with "ku" had already been lost.
It was two-fold.
That's a convoluted code for relaying a message.
A layman could never crack it,
but if the recipient already knew the
rules of the cipher, it would be easy.
To cut right to the chase...
I believe that was the plot of The Kudryavka
Sequence, the manga you were all planning to write.
You're wondering how on Earth I could know the title.
Isn't that right?
The Kudryavka Sequence is a take on one
of Agatha Christie's most famous works,
The A.B.C. Murders.
Same goes for the Jumoji Caper.
The culprit used The Kudryavka
Sequence as his source material.
As for the intended recipient of the coded message,
that's Muneyoshi Kugayama.
Student council president.
And the artist behind A Corpse by Evening.
Am I wrong?
Hmm...
Why would all the other targets be clubs, and then
switch it up to have "ku" represent someone's name?
Jumoji never wrote anything to establish
that all the targets would be clubs.
It's a bit thin. It's not that thin at all.
You put out a list, and implied that all of
your victims would be chosen from among those on it.
Copying the timetable bit from
The A.B.C. Murders was obvious.
I mean, you had a list already drawn up for you.
All the victims were together, right here on this page.
The Acapella Club, the Go Club, the
Fortunetelling Club, the Gardening Club,
the Cooking Club, the Wall Newspaper Club,
the Magic Club, and finally...
...Muneyoshi Kugayama.
Once I put it all together, it
wasn't difficult to trace back to you.
It's incredibly convenient that all the
targeted clubs were listed together on this page.
Only someone on the executive committee
could have orchestrated this page that way.
Fine, but there are 20 other people on that committee.
Yes. That brings me to the manga.
A Corpse by Evening.
President Kugayama, the author, had
teamed up with Haruna Anjo on this one,
so he must have known about The Kudryavka Sequence.
That means President Kugayama would also
be able to decipher the Jumoji Caper's code.
One possibility is that Kugayama lost the original
story for The Kudryavka Sequence, thus providing a motive.
Jumoji could have concocted this whole
scheme in order to exact revenge for that, right?
Meaning the message he was trying
to relay with these crimes is this:
"Kugayama has already forfeited his Kudryavka Sequence."
Now, consider this afterword:
It was written by the same person
who helped with the backgrounds.
Haruna Anjo.
President Kugayama.
Other than those two, only one other person
knows the plot line of The Kudryavka Sequence.
That person is the only possible culprit here,
and then there's this:
"Takuha Ajimu." That's quite an odd penname.
But it's just a mash-up of the first characters in
the names of the three people who wrote this, right?
How's that?
"Haruna Anjo" gives us "Ha" and "A."
"Muneyoshi Kugayama." There's the "Mu" and "Ku."
Take away those four letters, and you're
left with two characters: "Ji" and "Ta."
It has to be a second year or higher,
someone who was at last year's cultural festival,
on the executive committee, and
whose initials are "Ji" and "Ta."
We also can deduce that it has to be someone who knows
President Kugayama well enough to know he draws manga.
There's only one person who fits that bill.
And that would be you.
Jiro Tanabe.
Well done, sir.
I never imagined in my wildest dreams that anyone other
than Mune or Anjo would be able to crack my little code.
I'll be damned.
Expectations, smashed. Way to go.
Why did you use such a roundabout
way to send your message?
I think you know the answer.
Is it because of your feelings for Haruna
Anjo, who was transferred to another school?
That was a part of it.
It's also just that it was the cultural festival.
I was dying to pull off a well-executed prank.
Although...
...not being able to say it out loud...
That was the biggest reason.
Well, there's another matter I'd like to discuss.
I just have a small request to make of you, Tanabe.
Yeah? What's that?
I'd like you to buy these from me.
Thirty copies of Hyouka, our anthology.
Are you blackmailing me into buying
these in exchange for your silence?
Yep.
I'm actually asking the executive committee to buy them.
That's absurd.
There's nothing absurd about it.
This is Kami High's website.
That's a mail-order link, a place to buy
items from the cultural festival, right?
You could have the executive committee buy these,
then resell them through this link on the website.
I can't just agree to resell them without a good reason.
There has to be some kind of buzz about them first.
Absolutely.
But lucky for us, there's already
a good deal of hype around Hyouka.
What are you talking about?
Don't you know? Jumoji, of course.
The Classic Lit Club is going to be your final target.
I can help, and Satoshi Fukube will also
be an accomplice once I officially ask him.
You'll have inside men at the target.
You couldn't ask for an easier job.
People will flock to the Classic Lit Club
room to try to catch Jumoji at his last target.
The anthologies will fly off the shelves, creating a
demand for them online, and then you'll sell them there.
It gives you the perfect opportunity to
wrap up your scheme in a nice little package.
What do you say?
That's not bad.
Yeah, I like the sound of it!
A dramatic close to the Jumoji Caper, and
also providing items for the mail order site.
It's beneficial to both parties.
I'm glad we agree.
So how do you plan to aid and abet Jumoji in his crimes?
We'll prepare a proofed
manuscript, which will be your target.
Then we'll post guards to
surround it, so no one can get close.
Oh? Then what?
According to the guidebook, the
Chemistry Club is doing a demonstration
on what happens when water is
poured directly over pure sodium.
I saw a video of it once online. It
flares up, and looks pretty spectacular.
You don't plan on doing that, do you?
I do.
I want you to somehow get a hold of the sodium.
Once you do that, we'll need water pistols.
Some members of the Confection
Club are carrying them around.
You'll have to negotiate with them for one.
You sure play a dangerous game, don't you?
It's festival week.
Why don't we close it out with a bang?
All right.
Then after we get the sodium, I'll figure out a
way to slip some of it into the manuscript pages.
Once we sell enough copies,
I'll give you a signal, like this,
and that's when I want you to
shoot the pages with the water pistol.
But everyone's going to be watching
the manuscript like hawks, aren't they?
Yeah, that's true.
Okay, how about this: I'll get Satoshi
to put his cell phone by the door.
Just call it before you shoot the manuscript,
and it will divert people's attention.
They won't know what hit them.
Good idea.
What should we do about the confession note?
The room will probably devolve into chaos, so just
slip it into a copy of Hyouka and drop it on the floor.
That sounds good.
All right, well, you'll have to buy a copy to do that.
That'll be 200 yen.
You're quite the salesman.
We really are up a creek here, so I'm desperate.
What did you say your name was, again?
I'm Hotaro Oreki. I'm from Class 1-B.
Are "expectations" what pop into
your mind when you think about Oreki?
That's astute. What gave it away?
I can just tell by watching.
Only when it comes to you, though.
Fuku, were you trying to beat Oreki?
It's not that I want to beat him.
I just look up to him a lot.
But...
I don't expect you to understand that, Mayaka.
No, I think I get it.
Well, I really messed this up.
I forgot my main rule.
Databases can't ever come up with conclusions.
And so, the 54th Kanyasai closes without incident.
Although, there were a number of "odd occurrences."
Way to go!
Anyway, good work all around, folks.
I hereby declare the 54th annual Kamiyama
High School Cultural Festival officially closed!
I know this may be too little, too late, but I brought it.
This manga was written by someone whom I
believe will someday write a masterpiece.
You actually found a copy.
Yes.
This isn't mine, though. I borrowed it.
But Kochi, you already knew about this manga, didn't you?
Yuasa told you.
That jerk.
She did.
Yuasa said that you and the author
used to be close friends or something.
Friends? Yeah, that's right.
I wonder how Haruna is doing these days.
It's been a while since I've heard from her.
Have you ever read this manga?
I have to say...
I think I understand what you said a little better now.
That whether or not a manga is appealing
is ultimately a subjective matter.
I get it, but I still don't
think you're right across the board.
I mean, that would take all the hope
and fun out of reading, wouldn't it?
A Corpse by Evening is a perfect example.
It's a really serious title.
If I were only into gag manga, I
wouldn't even give it a second thought.
That's just how people are.
But if they did read it, they would like it!
Some works have a powerful impact on people, regardless!
On those with discerning tastes, maybe.
I don't agree!
I'm messing with you.
I'm joking.
Come on, I feel the same way you do about manga.
You're just too passionate to see it.
You're so sincere.
It's all bluster. Ayako doesn't mean it.
That manga keeps coming back to haunt me,
so I guess I'm supposed to have this conversation.
I haven't read the whole thing. I gave up halfway.
Know why?
I don't.
You told me before that I would understand if I read it.
And I get it, I really do. It's good.
But I don't actually want to have to admit that it's good.
It's all about my pride.
Say you had a friend who didn't read
manga, but knew you were really into it.
Then that friend teamed up with someone.
And decided to draw one herself.
So?
If it were great, wouldn't you be a little angry?
That's why I keep it tucked in the back of my closet.
I swore I'd never read it.
Out of spite and pettiness, I refused to open it.
I swore to always say that it was no good.
But fate just had to keep throwing it in my face.
Look, I'm sorry you went and got a copy
for me, because I am still not gonna read it.
Wait...
I mean, if I were to read it, then
I'd be forced to reach out to her.
And how could I bring myself to say,
"I read it, and you're amazing!
I have really high expectations for your next one!"
I can't make myself do that! You know?
That cat... It's from Body Talk!
A masterpiece is a masterpiece from
the beginning. It doesn't become one.
Body Talk.
There's no denying it's a step below A Corpse by Evening.
My stuff is a hundred steps below.
Is this pile really all that's left of them?
Yeah.
Whoa... Whoa!
I can't believe it!
I can't believe we pulled this off!
It's incredible!
We sold almost 200 anthologies!
I never expected to do that!
"Expected."
Interesting.
Oh... nothing.
I can't ever tell Chitanda that I
resorted to blackmail to sell these things.
Hey, Oreki.
Earlier, you mentioned you thought that the reason
I started this whole thing was to get revenge
on Kugayama for losing the
Kudryavka Sequence, isn't that right?
It was just a hypothesis.
I have no real way of knowing what
your true motive was in doing it.
Well, it's astute.
Especially because Anjo is the only
person who truly knows how I feel.
Wait, are you saying Kugayama has no idea?
Yeah.
But the code was invented and
executed with him in mind, right?
That's correct.
Then what's the point?
Ever since Mune... I mean, ever since
Kugayama finished A Corpse by Evening,
he hasn't picked up his pen to write again, not even once.
Anjo is brilliant, too, don't get me wrong,
but I had no idea Kugayama could draw so well.
I wish I had his talent, but I'm mediocre at best.
I couldn't hold a candle to him!
I know the story isn't lost!
I think that if he would just get his head in the
right place, he could create a masterpiece that would blow
A Corpse by Evening out of the water!
But as far as Mune is concerned,
drawing manga is something he just did once on a lark.
He did that on a lark?
It's such a waste of talent.
You think it's a shame, too, right?
But he doesn't have any desire to draw.
I would have been willing to do anything he
said, anything to help, if he would just agree
to continue working on it.
But I was too afraid to speak up.
I didn't want to admit to myself
that he might not recognize the message.
And out of that denial, my expectations were born.
I've been carrying them around this whole time.
But wouldn't it have been a lot simpler
if you could just tell him how you feel?
If you had asked him?
"Kugayama.
Have you even had a chance to
read The Kudryavka Sequence "?
You really are perceptive.
But you know his answer.
Oh, you're right. I do.
Mune never opened the story that
Anjo poured her heart and soul into.
So he couldn't have cracked the code.
My message didn't get through.
Oreki.
Here, thanks for this.
Tell your sister I said thanks, too.
Yeah.
What now?
Nothing. I'll tell her for you.
So what should we do about these four leftover copies?
There's nothing much we can do.
I guess we'll just have to buy one copy each.
And with that... we're sold out!
All that's left is to find the
truth behind the Jumoji Caper.
And now, since there's nothing standing in
our way we can use all of our brain power!
Or... not.
Oh.
Actually, Hotaro already figured that one out.
Leave it to him to crack it on his own.
Huh? Did he really?
Is that true?
Well... I mean...
Yeah, why don't you tell us
all about your findings, Hotaro?
We can have our own little selling-out celebration.
Oh!
Satoshi!
Come on, buddy, why don't we all have some fun?
I am so down to party!
I didn't get to spend much time with the Classic Lit Club.
So you have to tell me everything that happened!
Okay, why don't you guys all come over to my place, then?
All right, it's settled!
Wait, what's settled?
Yes! Time to get out of here and
cut loose! We are drinking tonight!
Now we're drinking?
Oolong tea, dummy!
That's the lamest thing I've ever heard.
Next time:
"Is the Mountain Range Clear?"