So, did you watch the show last night?
What show?
What do you mean, "what show"?
"The News Crew Saw It: The
Startling Truth Behind 'Hassie',
the Giant Eel of Lake Hamana."
Oh, yeah. I watched that, too!
Stuff like that always turns out to be fake.
"Upon seeing the true nature, he knew it was no ghost,
but a beckoning flower."
You're such a party pooper.
I think legends make life more exciting!
Chi, you with me?
I am curious as to the veracity of the monster sightings.
Nobody can say for sure if the
eel exists, but I hope it does.
It's more fun that way, y'know?
There are no ghosts.
Just beckoning flowers.
Classic Hotaro.
The Classic Lit Club consists of a whopping four members.
All of whom are now being bounced around on a bus,
headed into the wilderness for what will
surely be an energy-wasting getaway. Yippie skippy.
The bus's last stop is at Zaizen Village,
a place best known for mountain climbing and hot springs.
The springs are what we're after.
I've always been of the opinion that
during summer vacation, one should vacate.
But still...
We haven't been together long,
but I feel like the club's become a tight-knit group.
Since it's summer break, why
don't we all go to the hot springs?
Huh?
Well, what d'you say?
You wanna go?
Yeah... Okay.
The shuttle should be here to get us any minute now.
Wow. Great view from up here, huh?
Oreki... You okay?
You don't look so good.
Carsick.
Hotaro wouldn't be Hotaro if he
didn't find something to complain about.
The trip was only an hour and a half.
What a sad sack.
Hey, by the way, thanks for scoring us rooms.
No problem! I've got family who own an inn up here,
and since they're renovating and can't accept
regular guests, they said we could stay for free.
Come on, Oreki.
We're here.
Let the vacationing commence!
Hop to it, Oreki, or we'll leave you behind.
Let's go! I'm ready to check out this inn.
Thank you for coming.
Welcome to Seizanso.
This little darling is Rie Zenna.
And this is her younger sister Kayo.
It's a pleasure.
Nice to meetcha.
You girls are in sixth grade and fourth grade, right?
You've both gotten so tall...
Hug!
Sis! Careful.
Your rooms are on the second floor at the end.
Whoa!
Hotaro, hurry and check this out!
We got a good room. Look at this sweet view.
Maybe coming here wasn't such a terrible idea.
But I still don't know about the whole "club
vacation" thing. It would be a lot more relaxing solo.
Except planning a vacation takes so much energy!
Come on! Cheer up!
And don't forget that the only reason this trip happened
was because Chitanda organized it and
Mayaka hooked us up with a place to stay.
Hurry up, you two!
It's time for dinner.
You heard 'em.
Let's get some chow, okay?
I smell cheese.
Quiche? Gratin. Maybe fondue?
Or not.
Ready to eat?
Thank you very much for the food!
Be sure to save room for dessert!
Let me guess: cheesecake?
How did you know?
I could smell it.
That's amazing!
Not really.
So that stuff Maya said was true!
What did you tell them?
We're gonna set off fireworks tomorrow!
That sounds fun.
Yeah, Dad bought some for us yesterday...
Hey!
What are you doin', clumsy?
Oops. I'm really sorry.
Here.
Oh. Thanks, I'll just clean this up.
Did it burn you?
No, I'm fine.
Geez. Try to be more careful.
Man. I'm really stuffed.
No Satoshi.
He must've gone down to the baths.
I guess the springs are kinda
the point of this place, huh?
Oh.
Hm?
Funny bumping into you like this. Where are you headed?
Same place as you, I'd guess.
Where's Ibara?
I'm not sure.
She went off with the girls someplace.
I know this is out of the blue,
but would you mind telling me a
little about what your sister's like?
Yeah, that's out of the blue all right.
I guess that you're curious
because you don't have any siblings.
My sister, huh?
She's a real character for sure.
But she's also pretty brilliant.
I don't think I could outshine her in any way if I tried.
Wow.
But, of course, I've never
actually wanted to try, so. Yeah.
Anyway... What's with the sudden curiosity?
Seeing the Zenna sisters?
You'll think I'm silly.
But I've always wanted to have a sibling.
An older sister or younger brother.
Having somebody around I could always feel at home with.
It sounds like a dream to me!
A dream, all right.
She's wearing some seriously rose-colored glasses.
Having a sibling is fine, I guess.
But it's not like you're guaranteed
to be best friends or anything.
Oh. I guess there's no mixed bathing here.
Of course there's not!
Hm?
Satoshi's here.
Dad, Grandpa, hurry it up!
You're taking forever!
Whoa. It's bigger than I expected.
Huh?
Well, what d'ya think? It's nice, huh?
It's like the spring water is soaking through
my skin all the way into my bones, y'know?
Aren't you worried that your
bones are gonna get waterlogged?
I never knew you were such a funny guy.
Well, nice to see you cracking
jokes and unclenching a bit.
Is that Chitanda?
Oreki!
Whoa! What happened? Is he okay?
He overheated.
Huh?
Have you ever heard of anything so pathetic?
He'd barely even gotten in before he
drooped like a flower that needs watering.
Yep. That is pretty pathetic.
Sorry I'm being so much trouble.
That's what friends are for, right?
Come on, is it just physically
impossible for you to enjoy anything?
Apparently so.
It was probably leftover carsickness.
Must've been.
Is that Chitanda?
Hey, Oreki. Are you all right?
Not really.
You still feel really hot.
I can bring you a cold towel if you want.
No! No thanks!
I just wanna sleep.
I'm sorry for making such a nuisance of myself.
No, don't worry.
We don't have big plans for the
night, just telling some ghost stories.
Heh...
I'm sure it'll be fun.
If you feel better, you should come join us, okay?
Well. Get some rest.
Thanks.
It's not even eight o'clock yet?
Taiko drums?
The truth is, the inn didn't actually need a second hall.
I guess they've got their window open, too.
There's a secret.
A secret?
Long ago.
An old, brooding man came to stay here.
They put him in Room Seven of the main hall.
He said he didn't want food.
And he didn't want a futon.
And people should just leave him alone.
It was strange, but he paid in
advance and came during the busy season,
so nobody asked any questions.
However, that night, a terrible scream rang out!
Then what?
People looked up to see the shadowy figure
of a person with a rope around his neck,
dimly visible, swinging back and forth.
Rumor had it that the man had embezzled
money from the company he worked for.
Then what? Then what?
Will you stop that?
After it happened, guests who stayed in Room Seven
said that they could feel something in there with them.
They could see shadows mysteriously
appearing during the night.
Finally,
the ninth guest after the hanged man...
Tell us! What happened?
During the night, he fell suddenly ill...
...and died!
Oh, no!
Then what?! Then what?!
I said stop it!
Well, first, Grandma called in an exorcist,
then she had this second hall built.
So guests could sleep far away from the haunted room.
Where is Room Seven?
There. Look out the window, straight ahead.
It's that one.
We live down on the first floor, and we try
not to come up to the second floor very much.
Hold on!
I thought this was just a story.
You can't tell anyone I told you about this, okay?
A local ghost story. How quaint.
Hm?
Morning.
Oh! Good morning.
Good morning. Is anyone else up?
Uh...
I saw it.
What d'you mean? Saw what?
I was sleeping so soundly,
then sometime after midnight a warm breeze woke me up.
And when I rolled over...
I saw the silhouette of a hanged
man in the room across the way,
slowly swinging back and forth!
It's pretty rare to see Ibara so shaken up.
Satoshi's gonna be sad he missed out on this.
Thanks for breakfast.
How were the baths yesterday?
I thought they were fantastic!
Good, I'm glad!
Hm?
And I hope your futon was nice and fluffy, too!
Yes, it was perfect, thank you!
It doesn't look like there's one for Kayo.
Sorry you didn't sleep so well, Maya, but I
figured you could handle a little ghost story.
Hey, it's not like I'm scared of ghosts or anything.
But I know what I saw through that window.
And it was seriously creepy!
You really saw it? You're sure?
I know what I saw, okay? Creepy, creepy!
How could you tell them that story, Rie?
Dad said we were never supposed to tell anyone!
Who asked you? It's only Maya.
I don't see what the big deal is.
What's wrong?
Well... What Mayaka said she saw...
Do you think it was real?
What the silhouette of a hanged man?
Well, ghost stories are a staple of these rural areas.
They live on for generations.
So, what are you saying?
Do you really think she saw
the ghost of a man who died here?
No, I don't.
In that case, I must have been mistaken, too.
Mistaken about what?
I saw the same thing she did.
The shadow of a hanged man.
I woke up when Mayaka started freaking out.
And when I looked out at the
room across the way, I saw it.
Oh.
I thought my mind must have been playing tricks on me.
But if she and I both saw the same thing...
You both must have mistook what you saw.
Like in that saying.
The one Satoshi quoted on the bus.
It was nothing but a beckoning flower?
Mm-hm.
Well, if that's true,
what was it we were really seeing?
Yeah!
If you're so smart, tell us
what we were actually looking at!
Wait, why should I have to...
Oreki!
Investigate this with us!
Will you? I have to know!
I'm sorry, Chi!
I wanna help, but I promised
Rie I'd look over her homework.
You can leave it to us.
Oreki and I will get to the bottom of this mystery!
Isn't that right?
As if I had a choice.
We don't have to go far, anyway.
That's some consolation at least.
Okay.
So you saw this shadow-thing in the
room directly across from yours, right?
Yes, that's where we saw it.
How big was it?
It's not like it was huge, but it wasn't small either.
And the shape?
Well, it's hard to say exactly.
The color?
I don't know. It was in shadow.
Yeah, right.
Whatever it was, it was lit from behind so
it looked like the silhouette of a person.
That's how it seemed to me.
So then it was backlit.
Around here, the only source of
light at night would have been the moon.
That's what I was thinking, too.
And the moon was bright enough
that it could have lit something up.
Do you think that means--
The shutters.
So what time did you finish your stories and go to sleep?
About ten, I think.
And the shutters then?
I believe they were closed at that point.
Huh.
If the shutters were closed then, there's
no way there could have been a shadow.
Which means we've run into a little snag.
At this point, our best bet is to
check out Room Seven in the main hall.
This is so fun, don't you think?
I'm extra-glad we came to this place now!
And I'm extra-wishing we hadn't.
Hey!
Oh. Yes. Hello.
You talk.
Huh?
I really suck with kids.
Oh, okay.
Kayo, can we borrow you for a sec?
Oreki and I would like to have
a look around in the main hall.
The main hall? Why? What for?
We're investigating the creepy
shadow we talked about this morning.
If it's not too much trouble,
maybe you could show us Room Seven?
I'm really sorry, but I don't think I should do that.
If I did, my sister would get mad at me.
Okay, at least tell us one thing.
Is the supposedly haunted room still used for guests?
No, it's not.
In the main hall, the baths and the dining room
are the only areas where the guests are allowed.
So, the room's vacant then?
The whole second floor is used for storage now.
Please. May I go?
Of course. You've been very help... ful.
There, you see? She hates me.
No, I doubt it.
She probably finds all boys intimidating.
What a sweet girl!
Mm...
Is it a big problem that we can't get in to see the room?
Not so much a problem as a hassle.
This would be easier if we could inspect the scene.
Oh! I remember doing these, too.
Hm?
Morning radio calisthenics.
I went to them up until the year before last.
Until her second year of middle school?
Seriously?
We should check around the other side.
The ground's muddy.
Did it rain last night?
Yeah. A little.
In order to create a shadow that you
would see from your room across the way,
both the east and west side
shutters would have to have been open.
Excuse me.
If you're hungry, lunch is ready.
Well, back to work!
Thank you for joining us.
Just look at those two together!
It must be nice.
Having a sister, you mean? So
do you wish that you had one?
Yeah. Kinda.
So, find anything out?
No.
We're just getting started. I do have a theory, though.
Yeah? Then let's hear.
Huh?
Enough of this.
What are you three talking about?
It isn't nice to leave a buddy in the dark.
If you're so anxious to be kept in the
loop, then quit disappearing all the time.
We never see you.
I'm being polite, okay.
It's good manners to visit the hot springs repeatedly.
Is he making that up?
Ta-dah!
Well. Like my yukata?
Wow! It's lovely.
Looks great!
I finally got one at the beginning of summer vacation.
You've said you wanted one...
Can't say I'm impressed.
What's wrong with it?
You see the sash?
It's not the real deal.
Well, it looks real enough to me.
You're the last person I'd come to for fashion advice.
Check out the bow.
It's a separate piece clipped onto the sash.
I don't acknowledge that as a yukata.
I acknowledge you as ridiculous.
Is something the matter?
Hm?
That stupid shadow.
It's got me as jumpy as those other two.
Wanna go back to the same spring?
Sure!
The hanged silhouette.
It's the product of Chitanda's and
Ibara's false impression,nothing more.
Just a beckoning flower.
We're still missing a piece of the puzzle.
Let's walk back together.
Satoshi's here.
All right.
You finished eating at the inn the same time we did.
So how'd you end up getting here before us?
Well,
if you slide down the cliff behind Seizanso,
you end up at a spot right behind this spring.
Sliding down a cliff just to save a couple of minutes?
That's vintage Satoshi.
I don't have an explanation
that will satisfy Chitanda yet.
The source of the shadow is easy enough.
The question is, how did it wind up in Room Seven?
Hotaro, you're not gonna faint again, are you?
Hey.
Tell me about last night-- anything interesting happen?
Besides the whole fainting thing?
Yes, besides that!
Well, we all told ghost stories.
And I was surrounded by more girls than I could handle.
No, something more official.
Oh, sure. There was a summer festival.
You heard the taiko drums, right?
Taiko drums.
That's it! A summer festival!
That explains everything!
So? That mean something?
Ah!
I know what the shadow really was.
Probably...
I think it was a yukata hanging on a hanger.
Huh?
But why would there be a yukata hanging in that room?
And for that matter, why would someone
leave the shutters open to display it?
Displaying it wasn't the point.
So...?
It was hanging there to dry.
The yukata was wet.
The reason the shutters were
open was to let the breeze through,
so that it would dry more quickly.
But, why?
It rained last night.
That's not what I mean.
Why was it in Room Seven?
Because in a deserted room, no one
would see that it had been hung up to dry.
Except we saw it.
True.
But it's the family they were hiding it from.
The family?
The person who hung it there...
...was Kayo.
Kayo was envious of Rie's yukata,
and she wanted to wear it.
But I doubt Rie would lend it to her.
But why not? They're sisters.
Didn't you notice? Rie marks all her stuff.
She makes it clear which cup,
which radio calisthenics card, and which ball is hers.
That kind of person isn't going to
lend out her most treasured possession.
Oh.
But Kayo still wanted to borrow it.
So she snuck it out of the inn and
wore it to the summer festival last night.
This would've been around eight o'clock.
Kayo went to the festival?
That's my theory.
I saw someone leaving the place at eight last night.
And Kayo wasn't there when you
were telling ghost stories, right?
Yeah, you're right.
She wasn't there.
Unfortunately for Kayo,
she ran into some bad luck at the festival.
It started raining.
The rain let up quickly, but the yukata still got wet.
Kayo remembered that we would be
setting off fireworks the next day.
And Rie would surely wanna wear the yukata for that.
If it wasn't dry by tomorrow,
Rie would know what she'd done for sure.
The family would see it on the main hall's first floor.
And the other hall was where we were staying.
She couldn't use the dryer in the middle of the night.
So, she waited for everyone to go to sleep
and dried the yukata in the most
distant room on the second floor.
But poor Kayo's bad luck continued.
Moonlight shone in through the open window,
illuminating the yukata's silhouette.
And then, to make matters worse,
we started investigating the mysterious shadow.
Kayo must have been a nervous wreck.
That must have been her shadow I saw.
Sneaking between the sliding doors.
Kayo...
She put the yukata back early in the morning.
Unlike Rie, Kayo went to radio calisthenics every day.
It would've been easy enough to return it.
So that's it then.
I'm not going to tell Ibara about this.
I think it's kind of a family matter.
If that's true...
...then it means that the two
of them don't actually get along.
I mean,
a sister who won't lend you her yukata...
That's just how it is with siblings.
Sometimes you fight.
You know, I...
I wanted a sibling.
An older sister I could look up to.
Or a younger brother I could look out for.
Is Chitanda's idea of the perfect sibling real,
or is it a beckoning flower?
So hot.
You ready?
Yeah.
Well, maybe it's actually a little bit of both.
Next time:
"Let's Go To the Screening!"