No.
So?
Yes.
Hmm?
Man!
Yes.
One.
Huh?
What?
Sure.
Oh...
Okay.
Yeah.
Sure.
Even?
I am.
Yeah.
Look.
What?
So...
I do!
Yeah.
Good.
Sure.
I see.
What?!
Itchy.
Sorry.
Hmm...
Oreki!
Right.
Umm...
We do!
Hooray!
Uh-huh.
No way!
Hotaro.
Mm-hmm.
Coming!
Well...
Mayaka.
Mayaka!
No way.
Bitter.
Satoshi.
Perfect.
Hold on.
And two.
Satoshi!
Ibara...
Oreki...
Mayaka...
Ruthless.
For real?
Hotaro...
Hey, Chi.
Next year,
Seriously?
Oh, Oreki?
I mean it.
Trapezoid?
And three?
Hey, guys.
I'm sorry!
Next time:
Okay, fine!
Let me see.
Uh... yeah.
Yeah. Sure.
Hey, Oreki.
But then...
Yeah? What?
What, then?
Hey, Hotaro!
But still...
What? Hmm...
That said...
That's good.
Fine, thanks.
It's too bad.
Oh. Chitanda.
Satoshi, too?
That's lucky!
Three people?
Okay, I will.
It's finished.
Yeah. Sure am.
If you say so.
What happened?
No, I haven't.
It's admirable.
Leave me alone.
Why would they?
Never mind her.
No, nobody did.
It was Satoshi.
What if it was?
That's the rub.
Well, Hotaro...
I will help you!
The chocolate...
Ah. Oreki, wait.
Just after five.
Wait, which guy?
That's Nakayama.
I feel terrible!
You have my word.
I hadn't, either.
Hey, Oreki. Um...
And in my family,
or turns to snow.
Good luck to you.
Yeah, I remember.
Listen. Mayaka...
Yeah, last April.
That makes sense.
Okay, it's a date.
Who is your crush?
Does this mean...?
Shall we go, then?
He didn't show up?
And as a result...
Well... You see...
That's pretty big.
That's not likely.
Yeah, fair enough.
Turned down again?
There you have it.
Of course she was.
I'll go check now!
Please step aside.
She deserved that!
You think so, too?
Airport. Get ready.
...has been stolen!
She seemed annoyed.
What did you think?
She wasted no time.
I'm going home now.
Please, wait a sec!
It dropped too much.
How did that happen?
Mayaka. I apologize.
Where are you going?
Should we get going?
It's just appalling!
Yes, it is difficult.
It's kind of crooked.
Ah, that makes sense.
I'm so sorry, Mayaka.
All right, then, Fuku.
That's Satoshi's bike.
No, too cold in there.
How long was he there?
There were only three.
Or did I imagine that?
Please don't feel bad.
Do you have a suspect?
he'd have been caught.
Then the chocolate...?
But you are, I take it?
Oh, excuse me a second.
What? Classic Lit Club?
Three out of five, huh?
Excellent work, Hotaro.
Hotaro, be honest, now.
I couldn't handle that.
Hello, Mayaka? It's me.
I'll take the Viper Two.
I mean it. That was fun.
The one with the poster.
That's a great question.
Except for you, that is.
The truth is, last year,
I'm sorry I tricked you.
Let me get this straight.
Well, um... I don't know.
Well, I'll see you later.
Mayaka's labor of love...
She worked so hard on it,
I really wish that I had!
I won't forget about this!
Want me to show you where?
This is a definite change.
Well, we're gonna be late!
This is entirely my fault.
Mayaka will be devastated.
It was sitting right here!
Just keep your mouth shut.
Mayaka is awesome. Really.
Exactly. It's been a year.
So you refuse to accept it.
Is he trying to draw me in?
Um... Does this look level?
Okay, let's get back to it!
It wasn't in there, either.
Let me take over from here.
You just go home and relax.
I can have a good time now.
It's all about what I want.
It's supposed to snow today.
And the Industrial Arts guy?
Just so you know, Detective,
Fine. I guess I forgive you.
Really? So someone stole it?
Although, it is unfortunate.
You could try to conceal it,
I'd rather not say. Still...
Huh... That's what happened.
But that's so mean of Fukube
Have they forgotten I'm here?
I'll bet that was no problem.
I saw him a half an hour ago.
People who've passed by here?
I have to say, this is weird.
And you're different somehow?
Yeah. That is what I'm saying.
You'll take the Raiden, right?
Yeah. This is the new Satoshi.
I guess this means we're even.
Is that what you're telling me?
Don't you say anything, either.
Man! That sure was a good game!
It's more adventurous that way.
That's not a nice thing to say!
Also... not on Valentine's Day.
Fukube's late? Something's off.
Well, what did they look like?!
We'll plan our next step there.
I'm terrified by that prospect.
What are you going to tell her?
If that's how you really feel...
if you might have seen anything.
What are you guys doing in here?
This isn't your fault, you know.
Promise that you won't tell Fuku.
Way to work that joystick, buddy.
Good morning, Oreki. How are you?
So she's saying... what, exactly?
All right. I'll help you find it.
Isn't it possible that he did it?
Anything else you'd like to know?
Too late, you're out of the game!
For Chitanda and Ibara. By force.
I know that sounds self-centered,
I really don't wanna get beat up.
He would play to win at all costs.
Let's switch players and go again!
She probably gobbled all of it up.
He was on his way to the clubroom.
You mean the boy with the glasses?
Kindly give us back our chocolate!
So you're saying there's a chance?
Well, that leaves one more option.
How was it? My homemade chocolate?
For real, don't let it bother you.
Nakayama, from the Astronomy Club.
I'm trusting you with this, Oreki.
I did know who took the chocolate.
Well, I don't want to get beat up.
That's where you're wrong, though.
But I don't want to fixate on her.
So don't give it too much thought.
But I'm still not going to give up!
Is this how Satoshi usually fights?
Hey... toward the end of the round,
why did you charge in like you did?
Word travels fast. Chitanda, right?
We'll be able to find it, won't we?
But please just let me handle this.
But it was bigger than he expected.
There's truly no one else like her,
to play along like he didn't do it!
When will you give Ibara an answer?
It's the only one I know how to use.
What on Earth would I need luck for?
I carelessly left the room unlocked.
The odds are about one in a million.
I have a good idea of what happened.
Satoshi said, "it dropped too much."
he wouldn't have responded that way.
Then I'd have to teach you a lesson.
I'm no longer trying to be the best.
So one day I just decided to let go.
By the way, Chi, I've been wondering.
Do you have any idea where Fukube is?
Have you mentioned this to Ibara yet?
And it's definitely not in this room.
You're really getting into this, huh.
I think you fixate on your interests.
Did you really? That's such a relief.
Listen, I really need to talk to you.
and if stupid Fuku has any complaints,
I really hope you're right about that.
I'll wait for him a little bit longer.
Which meant his only option was clear.
It stopped being fun for me, you know?
This whole thing was just to test him.
I think my answer will come very soon.
He's changed a lot since middle school.
Today is... Well, it's Valentines' Day.
Sorry, you'll have to tell me tomorrow.
I'm sorry, but you need to hear me out.
Then let's use the east stairs instead.
and I truly didn't mean any disrespect.
Do I strike you as the compulsive type?
I wasn't obsessed with winning anymore?
I don't even consider how Mayaka feels.
I guess there's no reason to hurry home.
I haven't been here since middle school.
It turned out to be quite a bit of work.
Please wait! Something awful's happened!
It could start sleeting again, you know.
Satoshi. Let me see your drawstring bag.
I'll cram that chocolate down his throat!
I was sure he'd focus on evasion tactics.
She had to sample all kinds of chocolate.
Hey, are you on your way to the clubroom?
I can't say I identify with how you feel.
but it would make your movements awkward.
I am now giving Ibara's chocolate to you.
but no one was hurt in the process there.
"The Doll That Took the Long Way Around."
And if he still wants to give me attitude,
not in the way a lot of other families do.
but there was no sign that they were used.
I'm not as sensitive to others as you are.
But you also hurt Chitanda in the process.
I'm certain that he'll accept it this year.
So, what's she gonna do with the chocolate?
No. I thought something arose unexpectedly.
No, that's it. Thank you all for your time,
I'm never going to be the best at anything,
That's why you didn't accept the chocolate?
For all your deftness, you're still clumsy.
Then he got the chocolate from the clubroom.
Once that changed, I could enjoy life again.
So... Wanna play a game, for old time's sake?
It does me no good to tense up and overthink!
She couldn't manage to get out of Manga Club.
This fulfills the promise I made to Chitanda.
Ah, you're right. I had forgotten about that,
Well, from what she told me, it's complicated.
and I don't have much of a stomach for horror.
Were there any distinguishing characteristics?
Sounds like we've got ourselves a love bandit!
But there was one little problem with my plan.
So how did Ibara's chocolate experiment end up?
Even so, why would anyone just steal like that?
We just came to ask you a question, that's all!
You have no reason to be sorry, Chi, seriously.
So it couldn't be hidden under a guy's uniform.
I'm pretty sure that he's the one who stole it.
That's it, Chi. We deserve some cake right now!
Now you've heard everything that I have to say.
trembling with what you could call, 'sympathy.'"
Do you really think it could be in the bathroom?
Today was supposed to be a happy day for Mayaka.
And I still haven't figured out a real solution.
I didn't even bring any gloves. I'm such a dummy.
Right, and when did you get back to the clubroom?
It's completely my fault for having been so late.
and someone stole the chocolate while I was gone.
How can that be okay? To be so obsessed with her?
Satoshi, what clubrooms are located on this floor?
So that girl in the group over there, is that Oda?
Ibara's chocolate was a pretty decent size, right?
It would be easier with the girls' sailor uniform.
And don't even try to say that it was just a joke.
when they are truly passionate about what they do.
I'm gonna wait in the library till the sleet stops,
nobody came in this room with any stolen chocolate!
The moment I heard the chocolate had been "stolen,"
"Sorry. I now see I don't know anything about you."
When it comes to robot fights, hand-to-hand is best.
Did anyone start to pack up their things to go home?
I chose to be particular about not being particular.
but I don't want to take Mayaka for granted, either.
I left the room for a few minutes to look for Fukube.
You didn't even think twice about breaking it in half.
I guess I'm gonna have to tell you one way or another.
I want to be with her, there's no question about that.
Things don't work for me the same way they do for you.
Apparently, Ibara's stuck in Manga Club and can't come.
I take the chance that I'll revert back to my old ways.
I actually know who stole the chocolate, already, okay?
We were pretty much already in the swing of things here.
For now, I think we should just go back to the clubroom.
I suspected that Satoshi had taken it from the clubroom.
but to be more specific, I've given up any chance of it.
I didn't think about Chitanda when I dreamt all this up.
I feel really terrible that you went to so much trouble.
I ended up getting the chocolate back safely to Satoshi.
If there's anything I can do for you, please let me know!
Chitanda, there's no need to beat yourself up about this.
Why don't we start by exploring all of the possibilities?
Come to think of it, we didn't check the girls' restroom.
If he didn't hide it, and happened to bump into Chitanda,
I want to thank you for everything you did to help today.
What a crazy coincidence, running into you here like this.
You're wrong, and I can't
forgive myself for what happened!
Unless he had told the kid to
drop it at some point earlier,
Well, are you at least gonna
tell me exactly why you did it?
Making chocolate from cocoa
beans is just too hard, isn't it?
This is probably not something
we should share with Chitanda.
That's what I thought, but I
couldn't bring myself to say it.
I told Fuku I'd wait till this
Valentine's Day for his answer.
I don't know what time, but
Nakayama and Yoshihara stepped out.
If you strapped it to your leg,
the skirt would hide it easily.
If you don't have fun when you
win, what's the point of it all?
I think that he was just telling
a white lie to cover for Fuku.
Oda might have left, too, but
again, I don't know when they did.
Did any of you catch a whiff or
a glance of anything chocolatey?
I think Satoshi's going to be
thrilled with the whole production.
Is there any way to get to the
fourth floor besides the stairway?
It finally stopped sleeting, and
I was just about to head on home.
Did you see anyone suspicious up
here between around 4:45 and 5:00?
But we have to do everything we
can to get Mayaka's chocolate back!
My suspicions were confirmed when
we talked to the boy on the stairs.
But anyway, because of that, she
was able to complete her masterpiece.
I promise I'll get Ibara's chocolate
to Satoshi by the end of the day.
If I don't, there's no way I can
show my sorry face to Mayaka tomorrow.
I will chain him to a wall and read
every last word of this book to him.
In other words, the culprit is still
lurking around on the fourth floor.
I guess that's what it looks like to
put your whole heart into a project.
I ran into her coming down the stairs,
so we came up and looked together.
Man, nobody here got any Valentine's
sweets. You don't have to rub it in!
I think she's just going to have to
leave it in the clubroom or something.
It was sitting right there on the
table when I left to go look for Fukube.
I will find that chocolate even if I
have to resort to desperate measures.
I am the one who blew everything way
out of proportion in the first place.
It doesn't look like we can use the
west stairs to get to the fourth floor.
Fukube and I have scoured every corner
in here and all around the building.
Caring so much about the prize took
the joy out of it, even when I did win.
I'll just have to make the best dang
homemade chocolate anyone has ever had,
Heart-shaped, wrapped in plastic, and
about this big, or maybe a bit bigger.
Other than us, the Astronomy Club is
the only one that hasn't gone home yet.
You invented that story about the
Spider Society so I could escape Chitanda.
People like that will actually apply
themselves and not let others beat them
That means when Oreki said that the
girl from the Astronomy Club stole it...
There is. Do you know of any stores
nearby that sell fancy baking ingredients?
"This chocolate is a gift for you from
your devoted older sister, Tomoe Oreki,
The Classic Lit Club, Light Music Club,
Astronomy Club, and the Philosophy Club.
There are a few things I need to check
out, and I can't do that with you around.
Besides, if I let go of my new philosophy
and give in to my feelings for Mayaka,
But not as appalling as me still liking
Fuku after everything he has done to me!
You mean this chocolate, poured into a
form, cooled and hardened, isn't homemade.
we don't traditionally give anyone gifts
at the end of the year or in the summer,
There is a store by the market that sells
culinary supplies for professional chefs.
I won't say a word. And I'd appreciate it
if you'd stop giving me that devil glare.
This was the only way I could try to avoid
accepting a gift that I couldn't receive.
You sensed something had changed at the
arcade, right? I wasn't the way I used to be?
And if that didn't work, he was an awfully
sore loser who would throw tantrums and pout.
Call me a coward, but I can't bring myself
to until I've done all that I can to find it.
The old me wanted to win just for the sake
of glory, and I was a lot fussier in general.
Satoshi's gaming strategy when we were in
middle school was to keep his eye on the prize.
Satoshi probably waited in the boy's restroom
on the third floor for Chitanda to pass by.
The last thing I wanted was to be around when
Ibara got the news that her chocolate was gone.
I should have locked the door, but I knew that
I was only going to be gone for a few minutes.
It's just that someone stole Valentine's
chocolate from our clubroom, and we only came to ask
and the fact that she likes me and wants to be
with me is nothing short of a dream come true.
Unless you count climbing the outside walls,
just the stairs that were closed and being waxed,
What kind of culprit lingers near the scene of
the crime, casually hanging up a poster like that?
It wouldn't fit in his bag in one piece, and
there wasn't a large enough bag anywhere in the room.
Well, he was already on the stairs messing with
that thing when I left the room to look for Fukube.
I'm going to shove a masterpiece into your face
that's so amazing even you won't be able to turn it down!
If the Industrial Arts kid was on the stairs the whole
time you were gone, he would have seen who came and left.