Is that you, Sis?
Guess who's finally ho-oome?
I expect a big "welcome back" hug when I come out.
I think I'll pass.
After I've been away for so long?
What a heartless little brother!
Hm.
Is this a souvenir from South America?
Sure is. You wanted one, right?
No, not really.
This is unusual. Since when do you watch TV?
What about the paper?
I don't feel like working my brain.
Hmm.
Your calendar looks pretty empty.
My schedule is packed full.
Oh, yeah? Doing what?
Napping.
I know about a job where you can get paid
for just sitting there all day long. Want it?
Mmm.
Well? You interested?
That sounds like a "yes" to me.
I'll let them know to expect you.
Here.
You're going to need this.
Yes, Oreki residence?
Oh, hi Satoshi! It's been a long time, huh?
Yeah. I just got back.
Hotaro? Sure, he's here. Hold on a sec, 'kay?
Hotaro! Satoshi's on the phone for you.
Mmm.
Hey. You know that book I lent you last week?
You done reading it yet?
Mmm.
Is that a "yes"?
'Cause if you are, I'd like to get it back.
Mmm.
So, can I come pick it up today?
Mmm. Just stop by after I get off work.
Huh?
After I get off work.
A job? You have a job?
I don't understand. What's going on?
It's no big deal. I'm just filling in
as a lifeguard over at the municipal pool
for somebody my sister knows.
Ahh. Your sister. That explains it.
Still, the thought of you doing
actual work boggles the mind.
Well, anyway, I've got to get going.
All right. Maybe I'll stop by the pool for a swim later.
Suit yourself. See ya.
Bye.
Hotaro!
Hey! How's it going?
I didn't realize all three of you were going to show up.
I called the ladies right after we got off the phone.
I said if they came with me,
they'd see a truly exceptional sight.
Yeah, you did. So where is it, then?
Right there! The elusive Working Hotaro.
I gotta tell you, I'm a little underwhelmed.
Not me! We all get to hang out at the pool together.
I think this is going to be fun!
Yeah. You're right. Let's make the best of it.
Hey, you creep!
Unless you're looking for trouble,
you better keep your eyes off my girl!
Calm down. He wasn't doing anything.
Yeah, I was just standing here.
Sir, please take it easy, or I'm
going to have to ask you to leave.
What's all that about?
Whatever's going on, I just hope I can stay out of it.
Come on, sweetie, you can do it!
Catch!
Are you ready, Mayaka? It's coming your way!
And... go!
Here!
It's all yours.
You can do it! Spike that ball!
Huh? Spike? I... Oh!
That was a pretty sad showing.
Right! Penalty game! You know what to do.
Ah! I'm sorry! They made me!
You watching?
Whoo!
Ready, set...
Here we go!
All right, get ready!
Here... I... come!
Wooohoohoo!
You think you're funny, don't you?
Hey!
Time to switch up. You can take your lunch break now.
Hey, Oreki.
We were going to eat too, if you'd like to join us.
If I'd had a little more warning, I could've
made something a lot better than this for lunch,
but I guess it'll have to do.
Hey, don't look at me. This one's all on Hotaro.
Yeah, why do you say that?
He's a monument to idleness! Look in the
dictionary and you'll see his picture next to the word.
Then out of nowhere, he suddenly
decides to start earning a living.
He should've told us about it immediately.
Really. Why didn't you?
Heh...
Well, anyway. I'm glad we all got together like this.
It's been a lot of fun!
Mm. Totally.
I have to say, though, it's not exactly a perfect match.
What's not a perfect match?
The pool and Hotaro.
That's for sure.
Come on, you two, that's not very nice.
Swimsuits and Oreki don't go together either!
Yep! The sun and Hotaro, there's another bad match for ya.
The sea and Oreki!
How about summer and Hotaro?
Okay, enough already. Tell them to stop, Oreki.
Hm.
All right. Anybody else wanna get back in the pool?
Sounds good to me. I'll take
care of throwing out our trash.
I have a few more bites, but when
I'm done, I'll put our chairs back.
There we go.
Aww. One ice cream wasn't enough, huh?
Well, you certainly do have a sweet tooth, don't you?
All right, you win. Let's go and get you another.
That startled me for a second.
Yeah.
So, are you liking the job so far?
Sure. It's okay.
I've always wondered what being a lifeguard was like.
Look how fast they are!
I wonder if they're training to be
competitive swimmers when they get older.
You never know, one of them might even
win a gold medal at the Olympics someday.
Yeah, maybe.
Huh?
It all just comes down to what kind of person they are.
You know what I mean?
If they're special, they'll do something great.
If they're average, they'll just lead an average life.
And what about you? Have you ever wanted to be special?
Not really. I'm just a regular
guy, and that's all right with me.
That's not true. You are special! To me, anyway!
Huh?
And the same thing goes for Fukube and Mayaka.
You might not think of yourselves as being
special, but I do because you're my friends!
I'm not talking about subjective opinions.
Objectively speaking, I'm not...
My opinion should count too!
I don't think it's a simple matter of looking around
and categorizing everyone as either special or average.
There's more to life than that.
As long as there's someone, even just one person,
who thinks you're special, I think that means you are!
Oh. I'm sorry. I just, uh... I should get going.
Ha ha ha! Wait up!
That's not true. You are special!
My opinion should count too!
Okay, Oreki. It's your break time.
I'll take over here for a little bit.
So... Are you on break?
Mm.
Well, um... There's something
that I'm sort of curious about.
Huh?
Yeah, it has to do with the
serious business of lifeguarding.
You see the woman over there...
the one in the red swimsuit?
Mm.
She's the same one we saw earlier
when we were finishing lunch.
I remember that she had something white on her ear.
But then I looked at her again
just now, and it's not there.
I'm surprised you noticed something that tiny.
I notice little things about people sometimes.
I don't know why.
So? Why ask me about it?
Well, as one of the pool's lifeguards, we thought
you'd be concerned about the potential safety hazard.
If there's an earring lying around out
there, someone could step on it and get hurt.
So, anyway. I thought maybe you could look for it with us.
Find one earring in a place like this?
Is she kidding?
And you're sure you saw something on her ear earlier?
Yes.
Even so, before we start an all-out
search, maybe we should verify that with her.
[I thought of doing that, but, well...
I'm worried that I'll get yelled at.
All you're doing is asking about an earring.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Then how about you go and ask her?
Thanks, I'm good.
Hmph.
Please, I'd appreciate it so much!
Come on. Isn't this a lifeguard's job?
Well? What do you say?
Please help! I have to know!
Huh?
That jerk from before?
I don't wanna get him riled up again, y'know?
Yeah.
Tell ya what, I don't want to turn this into
a big deal. So let's look for it discreetly.
Sure. It'll be slow-going alone, though.
Right.
Well, you're not the only lifeguard we have.
I'll get the others to check the poolside.
As for you... you can start inside the pool.
'Kay.
Don't worry. I'll help look.
Yeah, same goes for me.
Well... Guess I'm in too, then.
Okay, thanks.
All right everybody, what's the
best way to start looking for it?
Our best bet's probably to split the place into sections.
Good idea. What do you think of that, Oreki?
Knock yourselves out.
Seriously, would it kill you to show a little initiative?
You're the lifeguard here, so that
means you should be the one in charge.
Just assign us to different parts of the pool.
Okay, fine, I'll take care of it then. So...
Chitanda and Mayaka, you two have the stair area.
Hotaro gets the slide area. And
I'll take the diving board area.
Well? Sound okay?
Yes, leave it to us!
Sure, why not?
Whatever.
Just curious...
Hm?
Why did you take this job?
Did you owe your big sister or something?
No, I just took it.
That's not really staying true to your motto.
What happened to "If I don't have to, I'm not going to"?
What's it matter to you?
All right! Better!
I'm glad to get a reaction out of you finally,
even if it is a pissy one. Much less boring.
Ah...
See ya. Happy hunting.
Oreki!
Doesn't look like you're working very hard.
I'm pulling my weight. I just found something at
the bottom of the pool and came to throw it away.
Sure you did.
You know what? Just looking at you right now is enough
to drain all my energy. I'm
practically falling asleep here.
So stop looking at me.
I'm used to being annoyed or
exasperated when I look at you.
This is different, though.
Either way, you're a real pain most of the time.
But do us all a favor.
Go back to being the kind of pain you used to be.
You're a lot more fun to be around when you actually talk.
More fun to be around... Huh?
Any luck?
No, none. But...
I don't think we need to keep looking anymore.
Ah! I know what that means, Hotaro.
You've figured it out, haven't you?
Yeah. I think I've got it.
Chitanda.
Are you sure it was an earring you saw the woman wearing?
Am I a hundred percent sure? I guess not.
All I can say for certain is there
was something white on her left ear.
What else could it be, though? There's no
other jewelry you wear on your ears, is there?
Right. That's what I'm wondering:
what else could it be?
What if we assume it wasn't
actually jewelry to begin with?
What? Now you've lost me.
Look at what she's doing right now.
If she were wearing anything in her
ears, would she be smacking them like that?
Sounds like it would be kind of painful to me.
What's your point?
I would guess that whatever she had on
her ear was probably something that got there
without her even knowing it.
All right, then. What do you think it could've been?
That's the question.
Satoshi. Would you do me a favor and pick Ibara up?
Sure.
Mm...
No! I don't want him to.
All right, what if Chitanda does it?
That's not gonna make it any less embarrassing.
I don't wanna be picked up like I'm some little kid, okay?
Well, that's a shame.
Since seeing a little kid picked
up is exactly what I'm after.
Why do you want somebody to pick me up in the first place?
'Cause I'm trying to prove a theory.
About whatever was on the woman's ear?
Yeah.
Hm...
I'm game if you are. What can it hurt?
Eh...
Ah, all right, you win. I'll sacrifice my dignity.
Impressive, Chitanda. I didn't know you were so strong.
What's that supposed to mean?
Whoa, hold on! I didn't mean it that way, I swear.
It was just, y'know, a general observation, that's all.
Yep. It fits.
What fits? Were you able to prove your theory?
It's her hand. She's resting it on your shoulder.
So... Can she stop holding me now?
Yeah. I've seen enough.
Down you go.
Look over there for a second.
Earlier, I saw the woman in the red suit holding that kid.
Exactly the way Chitanda was holding Ibara.
If he was eating an ice cream
cone like that at the same time,
what would've happened?
I get it!
The cone would've been at the perfect
height to get ice cream on the woman's ear!
And there you have it.
Ah... So that explains why it isn't there anymore.
Either it washed off while she was
swimming or she just wiped it off herself.
Case closed. Mystery solved.
You know, Oreki...
Yeah, what's up?
Well, um... It's just...
That was great! I think the way you're able to
figure things out makes you a really special person!
Heh. Flattery will get you nowhere with me.
Hm.
Sure.
And here I was starting to think we'd
never hear another snappy retort from you!
Would that be so bad?
You wouldn't think. But you were totally
weirding us out for a little while there.
Hmph.
Ah! Sorry! I just realized I haven't thanked you yet.
Thanks a lot. Sorry to bother
you with something like this.
I made a big fuss. And it was all for nothing.
Hey. I...
No, you shouldn't apologize. I mean, I'm the one
who thought it was an earring in the first place.
I'm sorry. Really.
Seriously, it's no big deal.
Alllriiight! I don't know about the rest of you,
but all this searching has made me hungry.
I could really go for some ice crea...
What's up? Why'd you cut off like that? Ah! Hyouka!
I seem to remember you solemnly swearing to me that you
would have your Hyouka draft
done by tomorrow, rain or shine!
Well, Fuku. Have you finished it yet?
Well, I guess you could say I have it more
or less finished. Give or take a page or two.
So the answer is no. It isn't finished. Is that correct?
Yeah. I guess you could say that, too.
That is exactly what I would say!
We're leaving! I'm taking you home right
now, and you're going to write that draft!
I don't care how long it takes, I'm not
letting you out of my sight until it's done!
Look. There's not much left to do.
I can take care of it myself, I promise, okay?
I don't believe you!
Sorry to leave like this, you guys, but
a deadline's a deadline. See you tomorrow.
Well, wish me luck... ah! Ah!
I hope it doesn't take too long to get the draft done.
Oh, I'm sure it will.
For those two, I think the thrill is all in the chase.
I wish they'd get to it already.
The thrill is in the chase, huh?
Well, I guess I dragged you along on a chase of
my very own, didn't I? Sorry I'm always doing that.
Yeah, seriously. You can be a real nuisance.
Hey, that's not a nice thing to say.
On the other hand, maybe that's not such a bad thing.
Huh?
Nothing. Just forget about it.
Oh.
That's right, I was wondering...
With that woman...
What gave you the idea that it was ice cream on her ear?
Oh, that's simple. Just look around.
Ice cream's the only thing in this place that's white.
I guess there is one other thing.
Huh?
Well. I should probably get going now, too.
Have fun. I guess I'll see you later.
Uh. Yeah.
Hey!
Break time's over.
All right.
Man, what a pain.