I'm sorry. I don't have it for you.
A Corpse by Evening?
You couldn't find it or something?
I must have brought it with me when
I went to the country on vacation.
Is that the truth?
Yes.
Fine.
Why don't you help with the posters, then?
The posters? Sure. Which ones?
Well... Start with moe.
I have to step out for a little bit.
I'm impressed. She remembered the title.
So Chitanda, Mayaka...
Don't forget that the cooking
contest starts at 11:30, okay?
Right!
I'm sorry, Fuku, but I promised that I
would help draw posters for the Manga Club.
What? Oh, bummer.
Well, let me see here.
If we move things around and
put you in the last position...
As long as you get there by 12:10, we should be fine.
That sounds great!
I'll do my best to make it by then.
See ya!
Well, I need to pop by the executive committee
room, so I'll see you guys around in a little while.
He's enjoying this way too much.
Hey!
Sorry, but would you mind
taking that box to the gym for me?
Sure, no problem.
By the way...
Have you had a chance to look around the festival at all?
Not really. I keep having to put out little fires,
but I have been able to do some exploring.
Why? Have you picked up any
interesting stories along the way?
Oh, man, all kinds of stuff has gone down.
Ah!
I heard a thief struck over at the Go Club.
What?
They stole some of the Go stones and
left a mysterious confession note behind.
Wow. I see.
You said the Go Club?
Yeah, but if you ask me,
I think one of their own members is to blame.
No.
There was another theft, according to Okano.
Apparently something with the Acapella Club.
Yeah? What got stolen there?
He said someone took a drink from their
cooler... some kind of juice, I think.
Did the thief leave a confession note?
Yeah, they mentioned finding a weird message in there.
Things just took an interesting turn.
What's up now, Fukube?
Why are you smiling?
Oh, nothing, don't worry about it.
Today's the day!
I've got this!
That's fine. I'll help you.
You're saying that I can leave them here?
Yeah.
Oh... Wow!
I appreciate it more than you know!
Better not say that until they're all sold.
So... How many, and what's the price?
We're selling at 200 each, and we printed... 200 copies.
That's a lot.
We meant to get 30, but we made a mistake, so we
need to sell as many as possible to pay for them.
We're desperate. We need help.
Why don't we lower the price of Hyouka to 150?
I'll sell them with the pamphlets for 200 total.
Great.
What's in the gym?
I don't know, probably something dumb.
What are you doing? I want a copy of Hyouka.
Oh, right. I was confused by your hand.
I'm sorry, but I didn't bring one.
From now on, you should carry a copy with you.
Your presentation is important as well.
Irisu...
Uh... What is it?
You're an expert at getting what
you want when you need a favor, right?
Uh...
Would you be willing to share
the secrets of your success with me?
What?!
What the...?
Yeah, okay.
First of all, no matter what it is that you're
asking for, you have to make the other person think
that it's their idea.
Their idea?
To do that, you have to set up an environment in
which they feel emotional contentment and trust.
There's a myriad of ways to achieve this,
but your most effective style would be...
...expectation.
Oh, yeah?
Yes.
Make the other person think you expect
this of them, and they'll feel obligated.
Obligated...
If you can do that much, their conscience
will do the rest and they'll commit to it.
They'll commit to it?
Yes, but you have to make the favor seem
like less of an ordeal than it actually is.
Like less of an ordeal?
Like it's not that big of a thing to you, but that
it will pay them major dividends if they agree to it.
One other tip, and it's a big one.
If possible, ask someone of the
opposite sex, and do it out of public view.
Right.
Now hurry along.
Get those anthologies.
Yes, right away.
Thank you. That helps a lot.
Trick or treat!
Yay!
What are you two supposed to be?
We're selling treats door to door for the Confection Club!
Would you like to buy some cookies?
Sure, how much?
They're on sale at 100 yen per bag!
Wow, you're packing heat!
How cool!
Ooh!
We could pretend to be robbers...
If you really want it, I'm willing to
trade you two cookie bags for that pistol.
Act now and I'll throw in an anthology for free.
Huh? Are you being serious?
Kerblam!
Okay!
Here ya go.
And as a symbol of our pumpkin-head
gratitude, have this, too!
You're selling flour?
Yay!
Trick or treat!
Kerblam!
The Manga Club's vaunted artist, huh?
Isn't that nice.
There. All done.
Mayaka!
All right, let's do this!
Is Mayaka coming?
She's still busy with the Manga Club stuff.
Oh, all right.
But let's not give up hope just yet.
Hey, Fukube!
This here is Suhara.
His dad's a professional chef.
Oh, yeah? That's pretty awesome.
Well... Do your best and I'm sure you'll be fine.
Bye!
We will do our best...
All right, everyone, time to meet our contestants!
Number one. Team Ajiyoshi!
Number two. Team... Fata... Morgana!
Number three!
Team... Astronomy Club!
Team number four!
Team Classic Lit Club!
All right! Yeah!
Here are the rules, so listen carefully.
Each team member has 20 minutes
to cook their individual dish.
After that 20 minutes is up, they
must pass the baton to the next person.
Team members outside of the cooking area are
not allowed to talk to the member who is cooking,
so keep that in mind and follow the rules!
Fukube, do you know what dish you're going to cook?
I'm really delighted you asked!
My special: Fuku hoisin fried rice.
That's great! Although, by the rules, we
would have to boil the rice from scratch.
So that means you'd have to be
our anchorman and finish us out.
No, I don't think my plan is going to work after all.
Since I can't make my rice, I'll lead us off
and get the ball rolling with some other dish.
Whatever you make will be great.
Now!
Each team member must prepare at least one dish.
Ingredients are first-come,
first-serve, in bowls in the center.
Once they're gone, don't worry.
You are allowed to procure others,
but only from on school grounds.
All that said, get ready for the first round!
To your kitchens!
Here goes!
Without further ado, let's begin!
It's Wild...
...Fire!
Fire.
Okay, everybody, Wild Fire is underway.
I don't know about you, Prez, but I'm certainly
looking forward to what each team will present to us.
Let's hope it's good!
Oh, Team Classic Lit Club is pulling the heads
off dried fish and cleaning each one individually!
That looks like some pretty precise work.
What do you have to say, Prez?
This is the kind of prep work that sets a team apart, VP.
Team Fata Morgana is doing great things with clam meat!
Is he going to make daikon radish miso soup?
Huh?! Fukube! You shouldn't be doing that!
You're supposed to peel the daikon first!
Fu...
Oh, no!
I forgot I'm not supposed to talk to him!
I've gotta follow the rules!
The daikon...
Peel it! Peel it!
Come on, Fukube!
Ah!
Did he figure out what he's doing wrong?
What?!
Is he peeling each radish wheel separately?
The water! The water's boiling over!
That looks like it's gonna take
quite some time, Team Classic Lit Club!
Don't get stuck in a loop, kid!
That's that.
What next?
We're still not able to tell at
this point what each team is making.
Uh-oh, Team Classic Lit is tilting his head!
What does that mean?
Ow! Hot!
Ah, I think I get it now!
He's making miso meat stew!
Looks like Team Ajiyoshi is preparing a basic meat sauce!
That sounds tasty!
There's no way I'll make it at this pace!
All right, lead cooks! Your time is almost up!
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
Time to switch!
Sorry.
I was only able to prepare one dish.
That's okay. You just leave this round to me!
For sure! Get 'em, Chitanda.
That's amazing!
Team Classic Lit Club is paring that
daikon like she's been to culinary school!
You're absolutely correct.
That is professional level work.
I'm impressed.
She could skim the skin off a pudding,
judging by the way she's peeling that thing.
That's amazing.
She's already completed one dish.
Well, that's Chitanda for you.
Team Classic Lit Club is hand-washing her rice!
They've already gone through all six liters
of water that they were allotted at the start!
That's an admirable way to do it.
The flavor of the rice is crucial.
Whoa!
Take a look at Team Astronomy Club!
What's going on?
If that's not a flambé, they should be worried!
Get the fire extinguisher ready!
Meanwhile... is Team Classic Lit Club making giseyaki ?
I sure love down home cooking!
Like mom used to make!
I've never even heard of giseyaki!
And, over at Team Fata Morgana,
the yellowtail teriyaki is nearing completion!
Brilliant!
Team Classic Lit Club is plating up that giseyaki!
I'm starting to get really hungry!
Just who is that second cook of theirs, anyway?
She's Miss Eru Chitanda, of the famous farming Chitandas,
and don't you forget it!
Meanwhile, Team Astronomy Club still seems
to be using an avant-garde cooking style!
Looks pretty far out there!
Team Classic Lit Club is rolling boiled
potatoes in starch and putting them in ceramic ware.
Now she's making imochi cakes?
This girl definitely knows what she's doing!
Oh... That's trouble!
This is making me nervous.
Trouble? What trouble?
No outside help is allowed, Team Classic Lit Club!
It's no use. I'm not getting through.
All right, teams, your 40 minutes are up.
Time to switch to your anchormen.
Hey, Fukube.
How'd I do?
You were amazing, Chitanda.
I had no idea you had such advanced culinary skills.
Cooking's fun! It's one of my hobbies.
Yeah, well done out there.
Although...
What's wrong?
We're already out of ingredients!
Mayaka. I'm sorry.
Okay, the time has come for
the anchormen to bring it home!
Finished!
'Scuse me!
Pardon me! Coming through!
Very nice!
It looks like Team Ajiyoshi is preparing
apples for a dessert course! Adorable!
Those little bunnies are taking
shape right before our eyes!
As of right now, Team Classic Lit
Club's anchorman has yet to appear!
Oh, my! Team Ajiyoshi is making celery roses!
Impressive!
That dessert is going to be a spectacle for sure!
Leaving Team Classic Lit Club and
their missing anchorman in the dust,
Team Ajiyoshi is making real progress
with their elaborate dessert scenery!
Mayaka!
What's this?
A girl in civilian clothes has just burst onto the scene!
Is she the missing member of Team Classic Lit Club?
That must be the case!
It's their anchorman!
She's finally arrived! Get cooking, girl!
Uh-oh!
Team Classic Lit Club is out of
the frying pan and into the fire!
There are no ingredients left to work with!
If she's unable to cook anything, then the
anchorman's score will be a big, fat zero!
After a hard-fought battle, could this
blow mean the end for the Classic Lit Club?
Is this really it?
Team Classic Lit Club seems to have found
a small onion. But is that cause for hope?
What dish could she make with that measly little onion?
She's just standing there. Could she be stumped after all?
What will you do, Team Classic Lit Club?
If you don't cook anything, your team will lose for sure!
What can they do?
What can I make?
I'm nervous.
What in the world could she
prepare with only those ingredients?
Now I'm curious. I have to know!
It's kind of your fault!
Team Classic Lit Club's anchorman
has still not moved a muscle!
And there it is, folks!
Team Fata Morgana has prepared a
fabulous omelet! Looks delicious!
Think, Mayaka!
You've got to think!
Has Team Classic Lit Club
finally reached the end of the line?
Come on.
There has to be something!
Team Classic Lit Club seems to
be out of options! What to do?
The time is running out!
Ten minutes!
That's not much!
Are they going to admit defeat and let the time run out?
Satoshi!
Listen.
Did you hear someone calling your name just now, Fukube?
What?
Satoshi!
Team Astronomy is boiling bananas in vegetable stock?
Excuse me, sir!
What is it?
Be quiet for a moment!
Satoshi!
Sounds like Oreki!
Look! He's up there!
In the clubroom!
Satoshi!
What the...?
Who is that?
Satoshi!
Get over here! Under the window!
Hurry up!
Go, Fukube!
Right.
What do you want?
Get ready to catch this!
Nice catch, huh?
So... What's this, then?
Team Classic Lit Club's lead
chef has reappeared on the scene!
What...?
Interesting!
He seems to have thrown her a bag of flour!
What a dramatic turn of events!
Checking the rule book...
Okay! It will be allowed!
All right!
Only seven minutes remain on the clock!
As each Wild Fire team enters
the final phase of competition,
Team Classic Lit Club has finally sprung back into action!
Under such impossible circumstances,
what kind of heroics will they need to save their dish?
We're all waiting with bated breath!
I know I'm curious!
What's this?
She's busted out the shrimp heads?
What could she possibly have up her sleeve?
Kakiage.
She's making...
...kakiage tempura!
Only five minutes left on the
clock in the Wild Fire competition!
How will it end?
Uh... Hey, you! Cooking Club!
You could at least provide me with a ladle!
The Classic Lit Club gets their
ladle and moves on to the next step!
The pressure is on for Team Classic Lit Club.
Can they hustle enough to rally
from behind and beat the clock?
It's kakiage over rice!
Will Team Classic Lit be able to pull this off?
There's only one minute left!
That doesn't leave her very much time to finish!
She scoops it up!
She lays it ever so gently in the bowl.
Three! Two! One!
It's over!
Oh, yeah!
Go, Mayaka!
Great job!
Yeah!
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing; don't worry about it.
And now, it's time to announce the results!
The hard-earned victory goes to...
...Team Classic Lit Club!
I'm exhausted.
It was undercooked.
Hey, with all the obstacles you faced, that was fantastic.
Yeah, but I had to wait for that ladle!
If I would have had one, it
would have turned out perfectly!
It took a whole minute for them to get one!
Idiot.
I should have known not to start
cooking that dish without a stupid ladle!
Hey, I'm really sorry about that!
I thought we had checked all
of the supplies very carefully.
We should have made another pass before we started.
Yeah, I thought that was weird,
and I should've said something...
Just slipped my mind, I guess.
That's okay; things were crazy!
Let's see...
No way!
What is it?
A confession note!
Next time:
"The Jumonji Affair."