Oh.
Me?
Hey.
Yes!
Yes.
Yep!
Nah.
Whoa!
Sure.
Yeah.
Okay!
What?
Yeah!
Oh...
Catch!
Man...
Right!
Three!
Three.
I win.
Galaxy!
No way!
Got it!
Not me.
Thanks.
Amazing!
My role?
Sure do.
Come on!
Nothing.
I'm Frol.
Oh, yeah?
One game?
Listen...
Say what?
Oh, good.
Oh, well.
All right.
You think?
Oh, right.
Hey, look!
The bunny?
Excuse me.
Oh. Ibara.
Oh, sorry.
Next time:
I wonder...
Cut it out.
Roger that.
No kidding!
It sure is.
You know...
Oh! Also...
Just a sec.
Same to you.
Indubitably.
There's 200.
You're here.
You're sure?
What the...?
Occult Club!
Good morning!
That's right.
It sure is...
That's right!
Thanks, guys.
That's great.
This is lame.
Good morning.
An old manga.
It's perfect!
No, stay away!
Apparently so.
Thirty copies.
This is great.
Is he serious?
Hey, gorgeous!
Fine, whatever.
Just for a few.
No, not at all.
That's amazing!
That's 200 yen.
Whoa! Hey, man!
This old thing?
I did it again!
You'll find out.
Two hundred yen.
All copies sold!
One! Two! Three!
Oh, I guess not.
Nice to see you!
What great luck!
You can have it.
Handicrafts Club?
Oh, good morning!
Yeah, good point.
I hereby declare,
Do you mean that?
Sorry about that.
Hi, there, Kochi.
Are you for real?
I have my methods.
Hey, are you done?
On the other hand,
Look. Right there.
I didn't see that.
Yeah, that's true.
Here's your medal!
Hey. Good morning.
Tomorrow's the day.
Hmm... now, then...
Yeah, you're right.
It's quiet up here.
So, what do ya say?
Is anyone in there?
Hey, wait a second!
Global Action Club!
It sure is peaceful.
What? A punk rocker!
Okay, I'll take one.
Um, yes? What is it?
How did you find out?
and the nib is split.
Sounds kind of shady.
Well, we'd better go.
In the mountain de...
Oh, hi. Good morning!
Yes. Forget about it.
Ward it off with that.
I think it's too busy.
And that refers to...?
You abused your power?
...is officially open!
Springtime has passed.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Oh, hey. This is Frol.
Uh-oh, getting sleepy.
Won't be needing that.
We're the Occult Club!
"A Corpse By Evening."
What am I, a trash can?
Yeah, I'm all finished.
Try not to dwell on it.
Nice of you to show up.
Right! I totally agree.
Wait... That's perfect!
Come try it! It's easy!
What a gorgeous poster!
Good morning, everyone!
I wonder what happened.
Is he really punk rock?
You want a magic charm?
I'm gonna go bother her.
It's almost time, right?
The problem is two-fold:
Please help us out, sir!
You're full of it today!
our school's Kanyasai...
So that's the situation.
Yeah, I finally made it.
What, like, all of them?
I've gotta see all of it.
Starts tomorrow, I guess.
Good morning to you, Chi.
To this! Let me show you.
This is our goal: Hyouka!
Everyone ready? On three!
Wow! He flipped over him!
The river from Tsukuhane.
That's way too dangerous!
Good morning to you, too.
What's your costume from?
He's actually a customer?
Wow, check out this mural!
Way too busy for my taste.
Oh, no! I broke my Saturn!
Listen. I'm sorry. Really!
Satoshi, care to weigh in?
It sure seems like you do.
This is amazing, isn't it?
I'm wasting precious time!
Tomorrow's finally the day!
You're up kinda early, huh?
You guys been waiting long?
Worst case, he tells us no.
And Satoshi will publicize.
When we laid out this plan,
No, I just bought the belt.
Oh! Don't worry about that.
Hey, there, how's it going?
Well, we certainly are now!
Anyone seen my apple juice?
This pen is just the thing!
It's cultural festival time!
Better go or you'll be late.
Let's give it our best shot!
I hadn't thought about that!
But what's your role, Oreki?
Hey, Calligraphy Club, guys!
Hey there! Do you wanna try?
Looks like I'm finally here.
Well, you've just found him.
Look who decided to cosplay.
I consider it a masterpiece.
I'll have to show gratitude.
Is there an Equestrian Club?
Yeah, I'm well aware of that.
He forgot what he looks like!
But it can't hurt to ask him.
Yeah, that's an awesome idea!
I'm gonna hold down the fort.
Hurry up and find your class.
Though I must part from thee.
Global action! Global action!
Okay, well, thank you anyway.
I've never heard of that one.
We're all friends here, right?
Now displaying the Enterprise!
Is today the cultural festival?
You sure are enjoying yourself.
for the 54th year in a row now,
Thanks! I really appreciate it.
Thanks for all your help today!
And after she made such a fuss.
Good morning, Madame President.
Thanks a lot for your business.
Well then take this as a trade.
I've grossly neglected my duty!
Hey! Isn't that Mayaka up ahead?
I like your outfit. Looks great.
It's terrible luck, considering.
I'll be back in a jiffy, though.
And how many did we end up with?
How much are we asking per copy?
This is just one part of it all.
That's right. It's a long story.
Hey, happy festival week, Mayaka.
Frol who? Oh, Frolbericheri Frol?
Did he forget what he looks like?
I guess someone has to stay here.
What? How does he spin like that?
What's that piece of paper there?
How would you like to be a model?
I heard you guys had some trouble.
That must be a Manga Club costume.
You know, that's a fantastic plan.
I think we should proceed with it.
Aw, I can't bring myself to smile.
Are you on Manga Club duty all day?
Now this is what I call a festival!
We haven't even gotten started yet.
That's pretty cheap, if you ask me.
I want to take charge of publicity!
I have something else up my sleeve.
So there isn't anything you can do?
The Quiz Club starts at one o'clock.
Nobody wants your crappy traditions.
Ah, the Hotaro we all know and love.
Did you come up with a costume, too?
So what character are you cosplay...
You can't change the past, you know?
Oh, how about the Quiz Club's event?
I did? Oh, I guess that makes sense.
I wouldn't have a problem with that.
But... I did want to ask. You see...
I couldn't even bring myself to ask.
It was an old science fiction manga.
that's twelve gone, without a doubt.
It's the day of the festival, Hotaro!
Did you spend a lot of money on that?
You think I could borrow it sometime?
Whoa, really? You'd give me this pen?
I guess he already has his own style.
Whoever made this did a fantastic job.
All right, people! It's time to party!
I'm so glad you guys are finally here!
Good morning, Fukube. Nice to see you.
There's no need for self-flagellation.
you should try the council room first.
Wait, shouldn't you be the one to ask?
She doesn't seem too eager to do this.
Is that why you're wearing that getup?
Then what character are you dressed as?
Well, I gotta leave you guys for a bit.
Creating another storefront altogether?
Who's the executive committee chairman?
He just wants an excuse to play around.
So, uh... What are you selling in here?
Glad I at least sold one issue, though.
Oh, no, oh, no, oh, no, oh, no, oh, no!
Would you like to summon a UFO with us?
I got stuck with the salesgirl position.
We're all responsible for what happened.
Well, I guess I could do that if I must,
You even have a katana for your costume?
Everybody makes mistakes once in a while.
I don't have time to stay and watch this!
You can keep it if you want to, you know.
Hi, there. Can I help you with something?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold up, hold up!
Sounds like quite the predicament. Hmm...
I can't be partial to you guys, you know?
The hall of fame for all the school clubs!
How many were we originally trying to get?
All right, it's official. Let's get to it.
I meant I can't just do that on principle.
I'm sure they'd let me leave some in here.
All right, everyone! Time to get fired up!
Man, I didn't even get to drink any of it!
We could ask the student council president.
I'll jump in to back you up if you need me.
Do you have a crazy brilliant plan in mind?
Let's try to sell as many copies as we can!
I'll reimburse you if you have the receipt.
Oh... Nothing. Uh... I just figured it out.
Or come see our spirit photography exhibit?
Are the others getting a good night's sleep?
I've got some gloves that I'll put on later.
What have you got in your bag? It's stuffed.
Chitanda will start worrying about you, too.
He had to have forgotten what he looks like!
but I don't have much luck with negotiating.
I'm going to drop the Classic Lit Club name.
What's up, guys? What are you talking about?
Do you expect me to say "thank you" for this?
Oh, I guess I should mention it's out of ink,
But isn't that a little bit dramatic, though?
You could at least consult the guide, Hotaro.
Okay. I guess I might as well give it a shot.
Haven't you ever heard of "They Were Eleven?"
Excuse me. Are you all open for business yet?
I mean, we're selling our club's anthologies.
I feel the same way about all the other clubs.
It's just a fake plastic one. Nothing special.
That kind of talk is uncalled for. Cut it out.
You don't want to miss our Launching Ceremony!
If I have time, I'll stop by and say hi to you!
If you have special circumstances, I'll listen.
Well, I am responsible for messing up the order.
The executive committee puts the guide together.
As much as I would like to help you out somehow,
That pen! Would you mind if I took a look at it?
I was just gonna throw it in the trash, so yeah.
I could really use a pair of blinders about now!
A Shogi tournament? Not sure I'm up for that one.
Besides, it's tradition that the Classic Lit Club
Chitanda, I think you should do the talking here.
So when I lay on the gas, that means we take off!
You have managed to blow my mind yet again, Oreki!
I called in a favor, and they came through for us.
Yeah, what of it? If you want to ask the chairman,
Chitanda will try to negotiate a better storefront.
Game faces on, guys, we've got our first customers!
Satoshi's probably the only one who would use this.
Of course I am! Why not? It's the cultural festival!
We'll set you up with a top-notch, stylish ensemble.
You know, why don't I just go ahead and buy them all?
Good. I'm glad you finally got your head on straight.
I wish you would have noticed the fruits of my labor!
Roll call for the opening ceremony is about to start.
I shouldn't have stopped! I don't have time for this!
That is a really good idea! I'll start asking around!
Judging by her outfit, I'd say she's on festival time.
I'd like a better storefront for the Classic Lit Club.
The Acapella Club is doing a concert in the courtyard!
Well, I am a member of the handicrafts club, after all.
No! I wasn't trying to make you feel guilty, I promise!
And I came here today to make a special request of you!
Please give the Classic Lit Club a better selling space!
Ooh! The cooking contest is definitely worth checking out!
Is our best shot really going to have much impact, though?
Well, even if that's all we
sell, I'd say we did all right.
May we have the perseverance
to climb the mountain before us.
After I turned in my draft, I
washed my hands of it for sure.
We will all proceed with the
plan that we have just outlined.
I'm in the Fashion Club, and
we're doing a runway show today.
and to create a more eyecatching
storefront in a busier place.
The whole school is really going
full out for this, aren't they?
So it'd help us to generate some
buzz about the Classic Lit Club
I keep getting distracted by
every interesting club event I see!
Well, don't waste any of that
precious energy beating yourself up.
I knew they went all out, but
this is better than I ever imagined!
I forgot to bring something to
put in my formalwear breast pocket.
can't get through a cultural
festival without some kind of problem.
You couldn't find anything to
wear on your feet that worked better?
I'll add our advisor to that, and
counting the one for the archives,
Who wouldn't want to see three
months of hard work go down the tube?
Do not use that awful word in the
presence of such respectable people.
There's not much time to discuss
business before the opening ceremony.
That's a good point! There's no
guarantee that our best shot will help.
I'll make the festival rounds,
participating in the events and contests.
Look, the Classic Lit Club is listed
at the end of all the club profiles.
I think I can go ahead and mark down
the ones we're definitely gonna sell.
I'm the club president, so I should
have looked it over before we confirmed.
If that's the case, you had better throw
me a good luck charm to ward that off.
Yes, actually, I'm looking for Tanabe,
the Chairman of the Executive Committee.
It's all my fault. I should have read
the email from the printers more carefully.
I was just trying to come up with something
to lure customers all the way up here!
Our club's lack of name recognition and
the fact that we're stuck so out of the way.
Sorry! Hold on! I guess I should tell you
that I'm the Classic Lit Club's president!
She should've just listened to Kochi from
the beginning. She'd have been better off.
Hmm... That's a special request, so it
depends on what the committee chairman thinks.
I was under the impression that Fukube was
going to be here to help me out with this.
If you keep fretting about what happened,
Satoshi won't be the only one badgering you.
Please let us have nothing but good fortune
at the cultural festival the next three days.
You don't think it'll be hard to get permission
to move on the first day of the festival?
Given the circumstances, it's safe to say
the Classic Lit Club members will each buy two.
The plan is to perform really well and to beef
up the Classic Lit Club's reputation that way.
If you want to talk to the other club chairs
and ask them to keep some of your books to sell,
if we don't give it our best shot, then it
certainly won't help, so we might as well try our best!
It's a VIP pass to our show, so if you come by
the club room, be sure to bring that thing with you.
I can't just hand you a better selling space when
you show up out of the blue on the day of the festival.
We've got our work cut out for us, so do any of you have
ideas about how we can sell as many copies as possible?