"Hey, Little Bro.
How are you?
I'm still in Varanasi. Congrats on passing!
Sorry this is late.
I hear you ended up going to Kami High, my alma mater!
Now that you're officially in high school,
let me give you some sisterly advice.
Join the Classic Lit Club.
It's one of the oldest clubs the school
has, and I was in it my whole time there.
From what I've been told, it
doesn't have a single member right now!
If no one new joins this year, the
Executive Committee will do away with it!
As one of the veterans, I
couldn't bear to see that happen.
Please, Hotaro.
Join the Classic Lit club, and help keep the legacy alive.
My adolescent memories are at stake!
It's not like you have anything better to do, right?
Sincerely, your sister, Tomoe."
1, 2, 3, 4!
It's been a month since we saved the Classic Lit Club.
I'm starting to feel at home
in the Earth Science prep room.
Good afternoon.
When I get bored after school, it's the first place I go.
I never expected to feel that way
in there, but I'm not complaining.
Want some?
I brought some snacks from home.
You're welcome to whatever you want.
Thank you.
It's not that I ever disliked
spending time with other people.
As long as they weren't the
kind who wore me out or anything.
It's pointless.
Yeah, is life like a dull pencil?
What? What are you talking about?
Was that supposed to be a joke?
Yeah, sorry.
Look. I'm not in the mood for jokes now!
'Kay, fine then.
I said it's pointless!
What?
All the time we've been wasting in here after
school every day, doing absolutely nothing productive!
I don't have a problem with that.
But is there something specific you want
to do with your time in the Classic Lit Club?
Yeah, there is.
Oh?
But... That's more of a personal matter.
She's said that before.
Right now I'm talking about something different.
If we're going to be a legit
club, we need some good activities.
That's pointless.
Wait, hear me out.
Let's submit an anthology to the cultural festival!
Seriously?
Yep.
Let's not. Sounds like a ton of work.
No, we have to have an anthology!
Look, if you really want to participate in the festival,
there are much easier ways to do it.
Like concessions.
Kami High's cultural festival has never
allowed students to sell concessions.
Anyway, they'll give us a budget for an anthology, and
our advising teacher has requested that we create one.
Also, it's been a tradition for this club to
create one for the festival for the past four decades.
They don't want to break that.
Well then, why didn't you mention all that sooner?
That means we have to do it.
Great!
So what is this anthology supposed to contain, anyway?
I have no idea!
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, sorry.
I thought that you and I could look into it together.
I figured if there were any anthologies from
previous years lying around, we could start there.
Why don't we search for them?
I give up.
Maybe they're in the library.
Let's check it out!
Why are you still sitting there?
You're coming with me.
Get up.
I'm not in the mood for this.
It's Friday, which means that
it's her shift on library duty.
Well, well. It's Oreki.
Long time no see. Can't say I've missed you.
Hey, Ibara. Nice to see you, too.
This is the sacred realm of knowledge.
Your presence here defiles all that.
Oh, yeah?
I'm floored they'd leave you in charge of books.
Do you even know how to read?
You haven't changed at all.
If you came to insult me, then you should just leave.
'Scuse me.
Hey, Hotaro! How's it going?
Looks like you two are as close as always.
Seems about right for the cutest couple in middle school!
Ridiculous.
Don't be disgusting. I'd rather
date a slug than this lowlife.
Out of your league.
Over the line, Fukube!
And you've got a lot of nerve making a
joke when you're well aware how I feel.
Ah, I'm sorry, Mayaka.
Hurt your feelings?
Do you even care that you're
pouring salt into my wounds? Not cool.
Seriously. Have a heart, okay?
I don't understand what's going on here.
She's had an enormous crush
on him ever since middle school.
Oh!
Ahem.
Chitanda, I'd like you to meet Mayaka Ibara.
We all went to Kaburaya Middle School together.
Nice to meet you!
Mayaka, this is Eru Chitanda.
She's president of the Classic
Lit club, which I joined recently.
Yes, indeed.
It's a real pleasure to meet you.
So anyway, what brings you two to the library?
Oh, right, I almost forgot!
So, uh, Ibara...
I was wondering if you might be able to help us.
I'll try.
Does the library happen to have any old club anthologies?
Like Classic Lit Club, maybe?
Let me see.
I don't think so, actually.
At least not out here, but maybe in the back.
Oh, okay.
So why are you looking for them?
We've decided our club should
make one for the culture festival.
So we wanted to look at past
anthologies to get some ideas.
Oh, yeah?
Are we gonna present it at Kanyasai?
I can't believe Hotaro agreed to that.
I was pressured into it, as a matter of fact.
"Kanyasai?"
Abbreviation.
Kamiyama High Cultural Festival.
Is this another one of those
terms you make up and try to coin?
No, for real!
That's what everyone here in
the school calls it, not just me!
Right?
Yeah, "Kanyasai" is what they call it in Manga Club.
"Kanya"?
Wait, how do they spell that, anyway?
I have no idea.
I've asked around but I haven't gotten an answer.
I bet it started as, Kamiyama High
Bunkasai, then shortened to, Kamiyama-sai.
Kaynama-sai. Kanyasai.
That's my hypothesis, but who knows?
Anyway, Chitanda.
There might be some old anthologies
back in the storage stacks.
But the librarian is in a meeting right now,
and we can't get back there unless she unlocks it.
I think her meeting will be
done in about 30 minutes or so.
Wanna wait?
What should we do?
We should wait.
You could always leave and come back.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait! Hotaro, hold up!
Hey, Mayaka.
You should tell these guys the
story that you told me earlier.
Huh?!
Hmph. Okay, fine.
Oreki.
Do you feel like using your
tiny brain for once in your life?
Nope.
What story are you going to tell?
It's called the "Most Favored Book of Disfavor."
"The Most Favored Book of Disfavor"?
It's quite a peculiar tale.
No matter how I slice it, it doesn't seem to add up.
It's got Mayaka and me pretty much stumped.
Please, tell us all of the details!
I report here for duty every
Friday after school, you know?
And every week, the same book
gets returned, like clockwork.
Today makes five weeks in a row.
That, in and of itself, is kinda weird, right?
This is the book.
Wow, what a gorgeous book!
It's huge.
Is it okay if I look inside?
Go ahead.
Oreki, you should see this.
It's about the school's history, huh?
I can't believe how dense it is.
This would be a lot of work to read.
It's not weird for someone to check this out every week.
They'd never finish.
You've obviously never borrowed from the school's library.
The check-out period here is a
full two weeks, instead of just one.
So why would someone need to get it more often than that?
Nevertheless, someone always does,
and turns it in every week, too.
Do you have a record of the borrowers?
Yeah, of course!
The checkout list is in the front cover.
See?
Huh? Oreki, this is odd!
Each Friday, a different person checks this book out,
but they always bring it back that same day!
Exactly.
This giant book has been checked out and
returned every Friday, for five weeks in a row now.
Even the times are consistent.
All five kids have come to get it
during lunch and returned it after school.
What do you think?
You're curious, right?
Yes.
I just... I have to know!
Let's try to figure this out, Oreki.
You want to?
Damn you, Satoshi. You knew this would happen
when you stopped me from leaving, didn't you?
I mean, you did such a great job
solving that locked door mystery.
And then there was that strange
business with the secret club.
Wait, what are you talking about?
She would be referring to a rather
provocative facet of Hotaro, here.
Stop, you're making it sound dirty!
In any case, this is curious, right?
No, it's not.
Yes, it is!
Is not!
Enough!
Be quiet. Both of you.
Right.
Sorry.
I got reckless.
Any further refusal could result in
a careless waste of precious energy.
That can't happen.
With that in mind...
Yeah, all right.
I guess I will think about it, okay?
Great!
Fukube...
Has Oreki ever been smart in his life?
No, not like us.
But he does have a knack for solving problems,
which can come in handy sometimes.
Hey, don't talk about me like I'm not here.
For five weeks straight, different people have
checked this book out, and returned it a few hours later.
Lesser minds might shrug it off as a coincidence,
but Chitanda wouldn't be content with that answer.
The truth isn't what matters here.
What's important is satisfying her burning curiosity.
Now, then...
Borrowing the book at lunch hour,
then returning it after school
doesn't allow sufficient time to read it.
If they didn't want to lug around such a tome,
they could just read it in the
library without borrowing it.
Conclusion: This book is not being
utilized for literary purposes at all.
They're not reading it.
What does that mean?
If a book's not being used for reading,
what other purpose could it serve?
If you stack them up, they make decent pillows.
They make good shields in combat, too.
Are you ever serious about anything?
He's right; These people can't be reading
it, so what could they be doing with that book?
Well Chitanda, what do you think?
Let me see.
Someone could use them as weights in a workout.
You guys are no help at all.
Is Chitanda really as smart as everyone claims she is?
She seems like a total doofus to me.
Let's try something else.
What does it mean that a different
person borrows this book every week?
Well, from the names, we can guess that they're all girls.
This brings up two possibilities:
The girls have no connection.
It's en vogue to have this book on Friday afternoons,
so they've all checked it out on
different occasions by coincidence.
Or, the five of them use the book together, as a group,
and they each take turns being
the one to borrow it every Friday.
"En vogue," huh?
For fortunetelling!
Right, like...
This book will be your lucky
charm on Friday, so take it with you!
If you check it out during your lunch period,
and return it after school, your
boyfriend will plant a kiss on you!
Heck yeah!
Astounding.
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
I'm just brainstorming here.
All they have in common is that they're girls
and second years, though all in different classes.
Why would the fact that they're all
girls have anything to do with this book?
Who knows, it might not.
Think about it:
If you randomly selected five students from this school,
there's a pretty decent chance they would all be female.
It's also pretty common for members
of the same sex to stick together.
Well, what if they're using it for some kind of code?
Like if they return it facing
up, it has a particular meaning.
Face down, then it means something else?
I don't think that would be a very effective code at all.
You see?
She's right.
Any face-up, face-down code would be lost in there.
Hmm...
Well, no matter how hard he thinks,
Oreki's not gonna figure it out.
After all, Fukube and I racked
our brains and couldn't get it.
Hey, what's wrong?
It has a peculiar smell.
Wait, it does?
I don't smell anything.
I swear, it stinks.
There's some sort of acrid odor.
It's like paint thinner.
It's unmistakable.
Is she a dog?
Well, if Chitanda insists she smells something strange on
that thing, then it's worth looking into, don't you think?
What could that mean?
Hotaro, if you've cracked it open, then you gotta say so.
Huh? Did you get it?
Calm down.
Maybe, but I'm not sure.
Hey, Chitanda, you wanna get some exercise?
There's a lead I want you to investigate.
Let's get right on it!
No, I'm not going this time.
It's just you.
Just me? Don't you need to go?
Well, I, uh...
Yeah, good job, Chitanda!
Hotaro has got no right to use you like that!
He's at his best when you're
the one taking advantage of him!
I'm not using anyone!
Oh, no, it's not like that.
I just figured we'd investigate together.
Right. That makes sense.
What are you waiting for then, huh?
Let's get going!
Thank you so much for coming.
We're honored to serve you.
We have prepared two fine menus for you tonight.
Which one would you prefer?
I recommend... this dish for you.
This might end up costing you more than you think.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
After all, gym class got rained out today.
So I think I have exactly enough energy to spare.
Great!
What kind of guy your age has such a deficit of energy?
Shut up.
All right, come on, then.
Right.
Hold on.
I'm going with you.
I'm kinda curious.
Fukube, would you watch the desk till I get back?
Huh?
I mean, I can't just walk away
from my library duty, right?
You hold down the fort. Later.
Don't have too much fun.
So where are you taking us to investigate now, Oreki?
To check out the art room.
Whoa, all the way over there?
Yep, it's far,
which is why I didn't want to go in the first place.
You have to be the laziest person I have ever met.
What's in the art room?
First let's set a few things straight.
I'm willing to bet none of those girls would
have time to get any use out of that book on a break.
It's too enormous for that.
Which means that they could only really
do anything with it during class time.
What are the only classes made up
of students who are in the same year,
but in different homerooms?
Gym and all of the fine arts subjects, right?
Yep.
So every week before class,
those five girls have each taken
turns to come borrow the book.
I still don't understand the timing, though.
I mean, they could check it
out for two weeks if they wanted.
The book is huge,
so they probably just want it
for class rather than lug it around.
Oh, that makes sense.
What is it?
It's the same smell as the book!
Seriously?
Look in the room and you'll see why.
There's the answer to your little mystery.
The second-year combined D, E, and F classes
are just using it in art as a prop
when they model for portrait painting.
The book's binding makes it an ideal, picturesque motif.
It was the smell of paint. Not thinner.
How did you figure it out?
Huh? What do you mean?
It came to me, I guess.
I just got lucky.
Wow, nicely done, my friend!
Students using it as a prop for art class
is the last thing I ever would have imagined.
I still don't know how you did it.
You're just... weird.
No, I'm not.
I'm probably the most normal person at this school.
Well... That's a bit strong.
Still, that's some really
impressive detective work, Oreki.
I'm completely fascinated by what
goes on inside that head of yours.
"Fascinated"?
Yes!
I'd just love to crack open your skull
and pick your brain sometime, you know?
That sounds like a horror movie to me.
Plus, to an honor student like you,
it's not that remarkable of a brain.
Oh, yeah? You're an honor student?
Let me put it this way:
We haven't had midterms yet, but I'm sure when we do,
Chitanda's gonna be at the top of our class!
No way.
It doesn't matter how good my grades are.
That can't compare at all to his raw ability.
Taking little clues and piecing them together
into a lead that actually pans out is just incredible.
Huh...
Well, on that note...
Her senses of smell and hearing fascinate me.
They're what solved this mystery and the last.
Oreki might even... be able to...
Hmm?
Uh... Oh! Uh... Nothing.
Anyway...
I had fun with this, even though I missed the best part.
What about you?
Yeah, I had a blast!
The afternoon flew by before I knew it!
I spent hours gripping over it
and I still couldn't even get close!
It's so frustrating!
Didn't I tell you he could come in handy once in a while?
I can't stand the thought of being outdone by Oreki!
My stupid life is over now. Finished!
Come on, it's not that bad!
It's odd.
Something just doesn't feel right.
I can't ever see myself acting like they are right now.
Why is that?
Is there something wrong with me?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Once he's got the scent, there's a brilliant
flash, and in an instant he knows everything!
Oreki, you can't leave yet!
Why not?
Oh, right. The anthologies.
Yeah, we have to wait till the librarian gets back.
Hotaro does kind of zone out sometimes, huh?
Not just sometimes.
He's always out to lunch.
Ibara, thank you for watching the desk for me.
You're free to go now.
Oh, good. It was my pleasure, Miss Itoigawa.
Ma'am. My name is Satoshi Fukube.
We're from the Classic Lit Club, and
we hoped you might be able to help us.
Where could we find the old anthologies?
Classic Lit? Anthologies?
You're in the Classic Literature Club?
Well, unfortunately, we don't currently have any
of the back-numbered issues anywhere in the stacks.
Are you sure about that?
If they were here, son, trust me, I would know.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm busy.
Huh. Well, thank you anyway.
I guess we're out of luck, Chitanda.
This is a big problem.
We'll find them soon enough.
So, Oreki.
Was it frustrating not being
able to solve a problem for once?
Not really.
Whatever.
That's that, then. We should go home.
I did learn something helpful today, though.
Yeah, what's that?
Nothing. It's a personal matter.
Oh, that again, huh?
Yeah.
Knowing Oreki, it might be possible after all.
Hello? This is Oreki.
Good morning. Um, it's Chitanda.
Chitanda?
Yeah, um, I'm sorry if I woke you up.
Did I?
Oh, no.
I thought it might be my sister or something.
So why are you calling on a Sunday?
I'm sorry.
But I'd like to see you today, if that's possible.
There's something I really want to talk to you about.
She's late.
Hi. Thank you for waiting.
I rushed right over.
Uh-huh.
So, was there something you wanted to talk about?
Huh?
I'm just curious as to why you wanted
to meet me here at this weird coffee shop.
You're the one who recommended this place, not me, Oreki.
Later.
Huh? No, please don't go.
It's my precious Sunday to do nothing.
I won't waste it sitting in this
place with you, playing these games.
Look, I'm sorry!
It's just that...
I'm really nervous, okay?
What is there to be so nervous about?
Are you about to make a confession?
Tell me that you love me?
There may be something I'd like to confess to you, yes.
Huh?
Next time:
"The Circumstances of the Classic Lit Club's Scion."