So that's when it all changed for Rome.
When the Romans overthrew the Etruscans
in 509 B.C., Rome established a republic.
The people were divided into two classes:
The patricians, made up of aristocrats,
and the plebeians, made up of common folk...
I'm so bored.
The classes were strictly forbidden from intermixing.
Now, the aristocrats held all important
governmental offices, such as the
two consuls, and the 300 senators.
Furthermore, the senate was considered to
be the highest legislative and advisory body,
meeting in the curia to convene and pass laws.
Did you hear that?
Yeah, what was it?
Is that Class A? With Mr. Omichi?
Yeah, I think so.
It's as if you have no desire to learn anything,
so why are you even here?!
It is Class A. What the heck's going on?
Sounds like Omichi snapped and
is on one of his tirades again.
Hurry up, we don't have all day!
What's your answer?!
Mr. Omichi...
Maybe you should look at the lesson
plan again. I think you've got it wrong.
Excuse me?!
Before you scream at us, you ought to be
sure you're not the one making a mistake.
Is that Chitanda?
Ah, sorry. I see where we are.
Tamura, you may sit down.
Okay!
Let's get back to the Roman Republic.
Let's see, where were we?
Oh, yes, the senate and the curia.
So the curia was a huge building
on the grounds of the Roman forum.
It was your idea for us to get
together in the first place, Fukube!
Hey, Mayaka.
Why don't you just try to calm down?
You should just stay out of this, Chi.
Look, maybe you did have a reason,
but it's common courtesy to call!
Or you could have even sent me a text at the very least!
I wouldn't have cared if you'd cancelled,
but to stand me up without a word?
I know you've got a cell phone,
so why didn't you use it?
It never occurs to you to do the right thing!
You don't care about anyone but
yourself, and that's the truth!
This is a big deal.
That's a bold move on your part, Chitanda.
Apologizing won't let you off the hook this time!
You're full of useless information...
Your efforts are futile, though.
You had to know how mad I would be,
but you didn't care!
Then it started storming like crazy!
Rain, thunder, lighting, hail! Hail, Fukube!
You're the most inconsiderate person I've ever met!
I even got all dressed up, like an idiot,
and by the time I got home, my favorite outfit was ruined!
Ruined, Fukube!
Aren't you tired yet?
Yes, I am.
Why don't you take a breather?
Fine, good idea.
I didn't intervene for your sake, dummy.
Wow.
I've gotta say, you get mad really often.
Does yelling make you feel any better?
You know, I only seem to get ticked enough to yell
when you are involved, which I think is pretty telling.
Yeah, makes sense.
You know, maybe you should take
a few pages from Chitanda's book.
She never gets riled up about anything.
Huh?
I've never seen you like that, either, Satoshi.
And come to think of it, though I've seen him get annoyed,
Oreki doesn't often get downright angry.
Not as far as I have noticed, anyway.
Fuku totally gets angry.
Yeah, I've seen him livid.
Do you really?
Of course.
I may not flip out and start screaming like Mayaka.
But yeah, I get mad.
I couldn't even imagine you having
that kind of reaction about anything.
Well, I am human, after all.
I get angry sometimes.
True, but you don't make a big production
about venting your feelings in front of everyone.
He's not very scary when he gets angry, though.
Are you serious?
Well, it's sure news to me.
That piques my curiosity. I want to see it.
What?
I predict that Chitanda will hatch some grand
scheme to trick Satoshi into getting ticked off.
Just to see if it's possible. I can't wait for that.
Oreki, do you have a secret temper?
There's no hot blood in that one at all.
Because he's so level headed?
It's more that he is way too selfish and
shallow to get upset about anything in life.
Hey, we may be frenemies, but that's over the line.
Whoa, I got mad!
Don't get me started on Hotaro; we'll be here all night.
But Chitanda's lack of irascibility is almost heroic.
She's like a Zen master.
Her patience is incredible.
No matter what, she always rolls with the punches.
You might be happier if you tried to be more like her.
That's easy for you to say,
but you don't understand what it's like to be me.
I don't think I could ever be a calm as Chi.
Hold on. I'm confused.
Is all this a compliment?
For sure. It's totally a good thing.
It's just an observation. There's no judgement either way.
Definitely.
Not being able to get angry is not good, but
the ability to rise above it is another story.
After all, wrath is a pretty serious sin.
You should cut me some slack, Mayaka.
The way you lash out isn't right.
A sin?
You mean the seven deadly sins?
Yeah! I'm impressed, Chitanda.
They're pretty well known throughout the world.
Hey, Mayaka, have you ever heard of them?
Yeah. Everybody knows about those, right?
Wait a sec, I thought there were 108 sins.
No, those are Earthly Desires.
Excuse me.
Let me see...
There's wrath, pride, gluttony, greed.
Envy, lust, and sloth are the three others.
Yeah, that's right!
Sloth, you say?
What's she looking at me for?
Wow! That means Chi is perfect!
You're honest, kind, and you don't eat too much.
I wouldn't go that far.
I doubt that you've ever been
greedy, and you're really diligent.
I am?
And another thing...
As for lust, you're not slutty.
Awkward...
There's no way to know if she's
envious, but I would bet she isn't.
This has turned from giving her
simple compliments into full-out teasing.
Let's stop talking about it!
Anyway, when I am hungry,
I can eat more food than you would ever imagine!
No surprise there.
I think her new nickname should be Saint Chi!
Eru Chitanda kind of sounds
like an angel's name, doesn't it?
The Archangels Michael, Gabriel, Uriel, and Eru!
I don't think this is funny!
She got mad.
You're right. She yelled at us.
Sorry, we didn't mean it, Chi.
I'm done talking.
Good job!
You know exactly what to say to make a girl angry!
Hold on just a minute! I think she's mad at you, too!
Just 'cause wrath is a sin doesn't
mean it's good to never get angry.
The same goes for the other deadly sins, too, doesn't it?
Pride and greed can be useful as
long as they're kept in balance.
What do you mean?
Well, imagine a person who has no pride whatsoever.
Doesn't that mean they also have zero confidence?
And if a person doesn't have an ounce of greed at all,
wouldn't it be difficult for them to
take care of themselves or a family?
And think about envy.
If people didn't ever feel it,
there wouldn't be as many
innovations, new technologies or ideas.
Oh! Um...
I didn't mean to go into lecture mode or anything, sorry.
Hmm... That's okay. Interesting take.
So they're fine in moderation?
I just don't think it's wise
to take the term "deadly sins"
so literally, and then live our lives as if those seven
normal human emotions are gonna kill us or something.
So then what you're saying is that it's
not necessarily a bad thing to get mad?
Yeah, pretty much.
I mean, if you always stifle your anger,
it might start to get in the way of
your ability to enjoy your life, too.
I definitely get mad.
But, like, if that's your philosophy,
then why don't you ever get mad?
Because it's draining.
And I avoid doing things that wear me out.
No!
Our Chitanda has been corrupted by Hotaro!
How could we have let this happen?
There are evil spirits roaming the halls of Kami high!
Ghosts hell-bent on conserving energy!
Please, Chi, snap out of it!
That's right, laugh it up, you jerks.
I'm kidding.
Huh?
I was just playing!
It was a joke?
And here I thought I'd found my twin flame.
Sorry to scare you.
I just thought it'd be funny.
But it isn't like I don't get angry.
Everyone does, even me!
Yeah, for example, I get mad when...
I get really angry when I see people wasting food.
In my house, a grain of rice equals a drop of sweat.
She's totally a true farmer's daughter.
Hey, I almost forgot.
Speaking of flying off the handle,
wasn't that you I heard yelling at
Mr. Omichi during fifth period today?
Yeah, you're right.
I can't believe I forgot about that!
I want to hear your thoughts!
Tell me what you make of my angry outburst today, Oreki!
Aw, crap.
Well... I gotta get going.
Wait!
Before you go, I just want to hear
what you think about what happened!
Did something crazy go down?
Yeah, as a matter of fact, it was crazy!
I still can't believe it.
In math... I got angry.
Whoa. Chi, are you kidding again?
No, I'm serious.
But I can't really figure out
what specifically made me mad,
only that I had gotten mad.
Ordinarily, I would have made
the choice not to have gotten mad,
but I made the mad choice, and now
being made mad makes me really curious.
Which kind of makes the being
made mad okay, if you think about it.
Have you gone mad?
I was made mad and then made curious about being made mad!
Never mind the semantics!
I have to know!
Go! Fight! Go! Fight! Go! Fight!
Today my class had math fifth period.
Mr. Omichi was teaching, and in a bad mood.
Oreki and Fukube, you guys have him, too,
so you know pretty well what he can
be like when he gets himself riled up.
I guess I should explain what
happened from the very beginning.
Let's see.
Mr. Omichi opened the door to the classroom
right as the tardy bell started to ring.
Before he came in, he stopped outside the
doorway and looked up at the class plate.
I guess so he would know what class he was teaching.
But that's not unusual. He does it every time.
Once he got in, the first thing he did was
write a quadratic equation up on the board.
It was simple enough, but he did something new this time.
He included bounds for X, which
wasn't something we knew how to do.
Then Omichi called on Kawasaki.
He told him to stand up in front of the
class and solve the equation for the range of Y.
Kawasaki froze.
He was confused, which is only natural,
considering we hadn't learned about ranges yet.
We were all nervous at this point.
Kawasaki said that he didn't know how
to solve for Y, which is what started it.
That's when Mr. Omichi flipped out and
started screaming at us for being bad students.
He calmed down after a bit and called
on Tamura, who is really good at math.
Unfortunately, Tamura didn't know what to do, either.
When the best guy at math in the class didn't know,
I got the idea that maybe Mr. Omichi
had been mistaken about the lesson plan.
The other students must have figured it
out, too, and things got a little chaotic.
Well, that really set Mr. Omichi off,
so he started being even harsher with us.
He even started beating the chalkboard
like a maniac, which had never happened before.
Someone in class may have been able to solve the
problem, but at that point, no one wanted to speak up.
Everyone just stared at their desks.
Then Mr. Omichi made Tamura stand
up again, and started berating him,
trying to make an example out of him, I guess.
That's when I just couldn't take
it anymore and had to stand up.
I told Omichi he must be mistaken and to
double-check our class's progress in the lesson plan.
So now I see that's the exact point when I got angry.
Well, what happened next?
Let me see.
Then he just turned the page in his textbook.
He saw something there and said, "Oh, that's right."
Then he apologized.
After that, he told Tamura to sit down and
continued teaching like nothing had even happened.
So that's Mr. Omichi's teaching style, huh?
Oh, for sure.
You would be traumatized if I went into detail
about the kind of grief that man gave me after midterms.
We had teachers like him back in
elementary and middle school, though, right?
Ones with really bad tempers?
Besides, your crappy grades are your own fault, not his.
You better study for the final.
So anyway, that's the story.
What do you think?
Is anything about that out of the ordinary?
Ah!
What I'm curious about is how Mr. Omichi
made that kind of mistake in the first place.
It seems so out of character for him.
He's usually kind of a perfectionist, so it's odd.
Yeah, you're right.
And I think the reason Omichi is so strict with
the students is that he's equally hard on himself.
So then how could he have made such a simple mistake?
That's the part I don't understand.
Yeah, weird. I don't understand it either.
Hey, Oreki!
Beats me.
Look, if you really wanna know that badly,
why don't you go right to the source
and pick Omichi's brain instead of mine?
Because that would take all the fun out of it.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I guess you'll never know the answer.
You might as well give it up.
I'm too curious for that!
Oreki, why don't you want to think about this with me?
Why me?
Come on, silly, don't you think it would be
fun for us to try to figure this out together?
Oh!
I don't like her talking to me like I'm a little kid.
Look, Chi.
You might want to avoid getting
your hopes up about this guy.
He was a sloth in one of his past lives.
What? Mayaka, you can do past life regression?
Nice distraction, Mayaka!
Interesting, but right now I want to know about Omichi.
Damn! She won't be swayed.
I just... I have to know!
Mr. Omichi always makes a point to write a
note in his textbook at the end of every class.
Why do you think he takes the time to do that?
So he can remember how far he got in each
lesson and pick up there for the next class.
That's what I thought.
He also does that weird thing where he looks at
the class plate before he comes in to the room.
It seems like a fool-proof system,
so how is there room for any mistakes on his part?
He probably writes the name of the class
and the date on the page where they stopped.
Like, on page fifteen, "Class
A, July first," or something.
Otherwise, it would be really easy for him to lose track.
Do you think maybe he could
have forgotten what the date was?
If that were the case, he would have
gone back a previous day, not skipped ahead.
Use your brain a little, dummy.
Well, she's not wrong.
Something's bugging me about this.
Wanna hear?
Of course, go ahead.
I can understand you getting
mad about something like that.
But I can't imagine you feeling so strongly about
it that you'd take the risk to talk back to a teacher.
Why do you think you did?
I was angry, but I didn't just speak
up because he was being mean to us.
That's not unusual for Mr. Omichi.
Then, was it that the people who
knew the answer didn't come forward?
No way.
Who would have wanted to solve it in that
situation, even if they did know the answer?
Could you have been mad that no one
else had the courage to correct him?
Uh, no.
Do you think you just felt sorry for him? Tamura?
I mean, I did feel pretty bad for the guy.
But I can't imagine why that would
make me mad enough to talk back.
It's kind of a regular occurrence that a
student who doesn't know the answer to a problem
we've already covered in class would
get berated by the teacher, isn't it?
But as far as what made me stand up to Mr. Omichi...
It's really hard to understand ourselves sometimes.
You're right.
What pushes Chitanda's buttons?
What makes her tick?
I still don't feel like I know her well
enough to be able to say one way or the other.
So what's your take? What do you think?
The clue about Omichi writing the
note in his book on the class's progress
is the one that might lead to an answer here.
But even doing that, he still made a mistake.
Since it's math, which is cumulative,
they're going in order, so there had to be notes
written on the previous pages in the chapter, too.
You're absolutely 100% positive that
your class hadn't learned about ranges?
I'm sure. Positive.
Well, suppose you had already
learned about them, then what?
I don't see what you're getting at.
Omichi teaches the same concepts every school term.
Class 1-A had the same lesson last year, didn't they?
If you're saying he saw the previous year's
mark and got confused, that isn't a possible answer.
How can you be sure?
The teachers' editions are replaced every year.
The publishers go through and make slight
corrections, put in new problems, et cetera.
In order to make sure they're all on the same page...
No pun intended... they just reissue them.
They're currently on the fourth edition.
I can't believe you know that.
If it weren't for us, all of
your knowledge would be useless.
Databases are never useless.
Maybe Omichi just wrote the wrong thing in his book.
It could be the case, but...
I doubt that answer would satisfy Chitanda's curiosity.
I gotta admit, I don't understand ranges, either.
It's all I can do to put X and Y in the same plane,
and even that's a chore, which is kind of pathetic.
I'm gonna be in for a world of
pain if Omichi sets his sights on me.
Wait a second.
Do you mean Class 1-D has already covered the ranges unit?
Oh, yeah. Mm-hmm.
So Satoshi's class would have been able to
solve the problem, but Chitanda's couldn't.
Mine wouldn't have, either.
Then that's the answer.
Oh, man, I recognize that look. You figured it out, huh?
I might have.
Chitanda.
Yes?
You're absolutely certain there was a note
in the textbook farther ahead than the point
your class had reached, is that right?
Yes. No doubt about it.
And it had to be one he's written this year;
it was just not on the page where
Class 1-A had actually stopped?
Right.
So what if we were to assume that the note was
on the correct page, just for the wrong class?
What if the note was a progress
marker for Satoshi's, not yours?
My class? Hmm...
Omichi teaches math to four classes, A, B, C, and D.
Even if the note wasn't for A or B,
that doesn't mean it has to be for Class D.
And even if it was for that class, why would it matter?
Well, if that were the case,
it makes sense that he would
mistake the mark for Class A's.
There's not much chance he'd
confuse a C for a D, is there?
Huh? Now you're talking nonsense again.
No one would mistake an A for a D, either.
But Omichi is a mathematician.
Yeah, so what?
That's why it's likely.
It's really easy to mistake
those two letters when you do math.
How?
Let's say on page 10 Omichi wrote,
"July first, Class A,"
then on page 15 he would have written,
"July first, Class D." Does that make sense?
Okay, so what exactly are you getting at?
Why would anyone confuse one for the other?
Just assume he did for a sec.
If so, then what went down today is pretty likely, right?
Huh?
Wait... I don't get how that would ever happen.
'Cause when you write equations,
A and D would look like this.
I get it! He thought a lowercase D was an A!
You solved it!
I guess you're right.
One time, on an English test, I lost points because the
teacher couldn't tell some of my lowercase letters apart.
Same here. It's difficult.
On my test, the teacher couldn't
distinguish the Ns from the Hs.
That's what happened. It seems so obvious now.
Man. I'm glad that's settled.
Huh?
D and A.
I can't blame him for mixing those up.
I feel bad now.
I guess I was a bit out of line
for getting so mad and yelling, huh?
I'm surprised I didn't get in trouble for it.
What?! How can you say that?
He was a total "D" and screamed
at the class for no good reason!
You have to stand up for what's right!
Hey, calm down.
Just look at how late it's gotten.
Don't you think it's time we headed home?
But wait... I wasn't finished.
I know, but why does it matter?
The mystery's been solved.
Hey! I'm not done with you!
Chitanda, who's usually slow to
anger, got mad today and had to know why.
She said herself that wrath isn't necessarily a bad thing.
But I wonder...
For some reason, she still
seems to avoid getting riled up.
Could her quest to pinpoint the cause of her anger have
been motivated by some desire to let Omichi off the hook?
Did she just want to find some proof that
she was wrong to get mad in the first place?
Is that the kind of person Eru
Chitanda really is, at her core?
Nah.
Who am I kidding. I don't truly know her at all.
Even if I knew her well enough to
make predictions about her behavior,
if I ever presumed to be able to read her mind, well...
I know what that'd be.
A cardinal sin. Pride.
One of the seven deadly ones.
Avoid those at all costs, they say.
I mean, come on.
How many times has Chitanda surprised me,
in this afternoon alone?
Hey, Oreki.
Aren't you coming with us?
Oh. Of course. I'm sorry.
Hey, listen.
Thank you for your help with everything.
I mean it feels like you're always
solving these mysteries for me, doesn't it?
Yeah, and it's becoming a real hassle.
What are you guys still waiting around for?
Yeah, you wanna live at the school?
No. We're right behind you.
Well, should we be going, then?
Sure.
I guess tomorrow I'll pick up where I left off.
C'mon, Oreki!
That may be true for you, Mayaka.
Think about it from her perspective.
And so, another afternoon of my high
school life is spent squandering my energy.
I've got my hands full with one deadly sin, sloth.
That's plenty for now.
Next time:
"Upon Seeing The True Nature."