Oh.
Yep.
Yes.
How?
Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah!
Okay.
Hey...
Great!
Right.
Well...
Really?
Not yet.
Hold on.
Hotaro...
Hey! Wait!
Seriously?
Just luck.
Next time:
Maybe I am.
Well, um...
I have one.
Uh, Hotaro?
This is it.
He told me.
Absolutely!
Wait a sec.
About what?
Yeah, maybe.
Just listen.
Yeah, right.
I don't know.
Jun Sekitani?
There you go.
Where is she?
That's right.
I don't know.
Yeah, me too.
That's right.
I don't know.
Yeah, well...
What's wrong?
Yeah, so am I.
He was a hero.
Oh, hey, Fuku.
Yoko Koriyama.
At that point,
And the title?
It's wordplay?
Oh. Uh, is it?
The thing is...
Oh, yeah? Good!
It's all right.
You don't know?
Seriously what?
Of course I do.
What, with her?
Come on, Oreki,
Not the future.
Which is why...
How'd I do that?
Oh, hey you two.
You all made it.
Okay, so then...
A long time ago.
Well, you see...
Come on, Hotaro.
Ice cream? Okay.
Of course it is.
"Hey there, sis.
Hotaro? That you?
Thank you, Ibara.
Very interesting.
Quite impressive.
I'm sorry, but...
It was just luck.
No, that's silly.
Have a nice trip.
It's for Chitanda.
Couldn't tell you.
It seems wasteful.
A sunny life. Huh.
No way! Seriously?
Hi, Miss Itoigawa!
Am I way off base?
I was wondering...
I'm babbling, huh?
I'll give it a try.
So not cool, Tomoe!
Wait, "the source"?
It's our librarian.
Yeah. Well, see ya.
That's pretty major.
Yeah. To you, maybe.
Well, say something!
By gaps I mean gaps.
Unless I'm mistaken,
Yes. I remember now.
Okay. If you say so.
Ice cream. I scream.
It only makes sense.
So, Oreki. What's up?
I still don't get it.
No, don't do it, Chi!
It's hard to explain.
So I thought, why not?
Sorry, what'd you say?
The dog is the school.
so how could we argue?
You really don't know?
It's got me wondering.
Your brother, Hotaro."
Hello, Oreki residence.
Don't underestimate me!
She felt sorry for him.
Here's the man himself.
Because Jun Sekitani...
I'm sorry to hear that.
a little bit at a time.
So is that really true?
I would be eaten alive.
That's always possible.
We're missing something.
So... No sign of Hotaro?
That's when it happened.
And then he also said...
This whole Hyouka thing.
Am I doing things right?
What? Are you kidding me?
You looked for her, then?
Right, library assistant?
Why, yes, I did write it.
A crazy curiosity monkey?
Yeah. That sounds grea...
I dunno. Maybe it's both.
It's her fault, all right.
I've still got work to do.
No problem. I'll help you.
I'm sorry, Oreki's theory?
Well, I'm truly astounded.
Did he make a brave stand,
How is that even possible?
Yeah, out with it already!
And thanks for the advice.
You surprised me, you know.
How are things on your end?
I've gotta figure this out.
What do you mean by "gaps"?
That's who you mean, right?
Hi there, Classic Lit Club.
How is he doing these days?
The rest of us did nothing.
But, despite our cowardice,
Nobody ever figured it out?
Hey. You guys... I don't...
If that day came... Then...
It's an incredible outline!
If what you suspect is true,
It's a little late for th...
Oh, really, your uncle, huh?
What exactly does that mean?
rather than the normal five.
"Committing a Cardinal Sin."
Well, let's get on with this.
Just admit it. You're pumped!
You see ma'am, he's my uncle.
The whole school was on edge.
The rabbits are the students.
Now... I can let my uncle go.
That's just my way of living.
And I don't like that feeling.
That's who you mean, isn't it?
Nothing right now. I gotta go!
What did you wanna talk about?
Would you please just tell us?
But the year I started school,
When this whole thing started,
Is "Kanyasai" still off-limits?
Look at this. What does it say?
The sacrifices that were made."
Why they chose the name Hyouka.
Well, whatever the case may be,
Rather than involve the police,
Yeah, I didn't expect it either.
Nothing in particular to report.
Well... I'm not so sure anymore.
Sorry. I meant curiosity junkie.
It was a very long time ago now,
And in the end, we went too far.
The origin of the term Kanyasai.
He said that I had to be strong.
And that's why I started to cry.
I remember. Finally, I remember!
You know, I'm kind of surprised.
Y'know... You surprised me, too.
Sure. Honestly, it was kinda fun.
"The struggles that were endured.
Does it really mean "sacrifices"?
Wow, you are freaky good at this.
Yes, that's my conjecture anyway.
You see right through things, eh?
Sekitani never broke his silence.
Now it only lasts for three days.
You know, I've noticed something.
I know it's a big responsibility.
Just get to work on your outline.
I'm surprised she isn't exhausted.
Same thing goes for you and Ibara.
I mean... All I wanna do is relax.
Chitanda's search for the truth...
Am I cut out for that kinda thing?
Hey, sis, you're still alive, huh?
I just reached Pristina yesterday.
There's a name that takes me back!
What a tragedy, huh? The poor kid.
It's the whole Jun Sekitani thing.
Not true. We can go to the source.
The person who wrote the foreword.
Actually, it's almost time for it.
Jun Sekitani drew the short straw.
But he never made his name public.
I mean... The message was obvious.
Like I said before, it's wordplay.
And it's all thanks to you, Oreki.
Thank you so very much. I mean it!
Maybe it'll make for a nice change.
So his story is still going around.
But is that really how it happened?
Why it was in no way a heroic tale.
In fact, I've confirmed it already.
but I still remember it so clearly.
Wanna tell us what you're thinking?
I think it's "ice cream." Isn't it?
That's okay. I can understand that.
Is that why you wanted me to do it?
Just something I picked up, I guess.
Don't waste time complaining, Oreki.
Well at least we solved the mystery.
All of you just do so much, you know?
We've been looking into Jun Sekitani.
It's either incorrect, or incomplete.
Or at least that's how I imagined it.
High school's all sunshine and roses.
What's more, sis called it a tragedy.
Sounds like they were very committed.
Hyouka is wordplay, plain and simple.
That's not much of a message, though.
I was terrified of being eaten alive.
We don't want him getting complacent.
About how we would probably need help
The so-called kindhearted hero, right?
People hung banners and made speeches.
I don't understand what you're saying.
It all depends on how you say it, huh?
you're the one who solved the mystery.
It's the anthology's featured article.
I want to live my life in the present.
I'll go ahead and wrap this letter up.
We're working on the anthology. Hyouka.
You called us in to say you don't know?
during the protest all those years ago.
so we were throwing a tantrum about it.
they conducted their own investigation.
You know I'm an energy conservationist.
I mean, you could've bailed on us today.
Is that the type of person I want to be?
Wait. Off-limits? Tragedy? The poor kid?
Thank you again for your help yesterday.
Originally the two meant the same thing.
Our resident academic genius has spoken.
I was right. She's got the info we need.
Either way, Oreki, that's not very nice.
No! It's like you witnessed it yourself.
Nobody wanted to be the official leader.
Jun Sekitani's battle for the Kanyasai...
It starts with the character for "alive."
Miss Itoigawa... Will you please tell us?
Honestly, it wasn't as noble as all that.
Is that because it was rebuilt back then?
How do you translate Hyouka into English?
He was totally happy to fall on his sword.
It can also be read as "offerings," right?
Except "offerings" is spelled differently.
We'll find out what happened 45 years ago.
So... You're the one who wrote this, then?
that restless energy became more agitated,
And that if I was ever weak, if someday...
It's the longest story in the whole thing.
You think I can't survive a mugging or two?
I presented my theory to the others, but...
A lot closer than you would probably think.
I still have a bit of shelving to get done.
You don't mind if we talk out here, do you?
I would like to see him again so very much.
Why is the club's anthology called Hyouka ?
The way "Kanya" is written in "Kanyasai"...
What does it even mean to have a sunny life?
But before we go any further, Miss Itoigawa,
I'm surprised to see it unearthed like this.
He left for India, and then he went missing.
Just what happened here all those years ago?
They cried out about injustice and autonomy,
That's how it seems, looking back on it now.
We just sat back and watched as it happened.
That's what you wanted to know about, right?
Except calling it that's kind of misleading,
I can't pretend those feelings don't matter.
What else can you tell me about Jun Sekitani?
And also, what really happened to your uncle.
Jun Sekitani. That name brings back memories.
for the greater good of the protest movement?
We're still missing that piece of the puzzle.
If it does mean something, I don't know what.
Sorry, I'm still trying to figure it all out.
Maybe I'm just tired of my little black cloud.
Except relaxing's begun to feel boring lately.
Then there's my sister, the queen of sunshine.
Hold on a sec, I'm talking about Jun Sekitani.
The fire spread to the combat sports building.
Jun Sekitani wouldn't have any regrets. But me?
That doesn't exactly sound sunny or rosy to me.
Why don't we talk about this more in my office?
And then, as part of a demonstration one night,
we built a bonfire to show how serious we were.
I've got a question about this special feature.
How did I end up being in charge of writing it?
"Anyway, that's all I've got to report for now.
I can't believe he's actually calling a meeting.
Okay, great, so it could mean one of two things.
She has a unique way of spelling her first name.
We should probably start heading to the library.
hoping to bend the administration to their will.
the school couldn't possibly look the other way.
And the rabbit fighting the dog is Jun Sekitani.
The real statement that Jun Sekitani was making.
The Truth that was Hidden for Forty-Five years."
I wouldn't have thought there'd be any reason to.
If Chitanda wasn't such a crazy curiosity monkey,
I assume that answers the question for you, then.
Sekitani could sense he was going to be expelled,
Where'd you learn to make a storyboard like this?
Now, Fuku, about the article you'll be writing...
How much did you know about the Classic Lit Club?
At the end of the day, is that really what I want?
I don't think we've completely settled it all yet.
There's just one thing I'm not totally sure about.
something that would resonate for decades to come.
Wow, thanks for putting all this together, Mayaka!
If I hadn't joined the Classic Lit Club this year,
Why do something like that if not to help Chitanda?
Are you suggesting that your theory was incomplete?
If we go and ask Miss Itoigawa about all of this...
I think I might know what it is you want to ask me.
Does it stand for "Sekitani" instead of "Kamiyama"?
The one you call "The Case of the Kindhearted Hero:
Did you know I'd start wondering about this stuff?"
I guess this means that, somewhere, pigs are flying.
We read that but excluded it from our deliberations.
I set up an appointment so we could all talk to her.
What you describe is almost exactly how it happened.
That year the principal dropped a bombshell, saying:
That announcement triggered an unprecedented uproar.
He wound up as the scapegoat for the whole movement.
He said that it was the only thing left he could do.
I'm writing because I've got some questions for you.
Put it how you want. You do this stuff 'cause of her.
Why the picture on the anthology cover is what it is.
I probably wouldn't have given that a second thought.
So you got marching orders from Hotaro too, I take it?
I hope it doesn't take long. I'm busy with Manga Club.
Yeah, but I think maybe we shouldn't have excluded it.
She's Yoko Itoigawa, but she used to be Yoko Koriyama.
So nobody needs to go poking around in my brain, okay?
Why was the story involving my uncle not a heroic one?
Everyone else did the real work. I just summarized it.
The high school cultural festival was a very big deal.
Yes. If a day ever came when I couldn't even scream...
No. It can be read as either "sacrifice" or "offering."
So he put it right there in the title of the anthology.
And I think I know why you're going to all this trouble.
I'm starting to wonder if you might have the right idea.
How much of Oreki's theory about the protest is correct?
and using the festival as an outlet for self-expression.
and we found ourselves at the edge of a full-blown riot.
I'll send another letter that way once I get to Sarajevo.
Despite firefighting efforts, it was partially destroyed.
If you'd prefer, I can try to take it on myself, instead.
Was Jun Sekitani's high school life really all that sunny?
why are you kids so interested in what happened back then?
So 20 years ago when the rest of the school was remodeled,
But I'm just not sure that's a gamble I'm willing to take.
Sometimes when I watch you
guys, it makes me feel restless.
I'll really get invested in
something, the way you guys do.
So that's the kind of trouble
you're getting yourself into.
For a lot of kids, it seemed
like the only purpose in life.
since Jun Sekitani was really
more of a victim than a hero.
and he was uncharacteristically
intent on using that title,
That you accepted the anthology
assignment Mayaka gave you.
If you know what Hyouka means,
will you please just tell us?
I guess Jun Sekitani would
know all about that, wouldn't he?
Because it seemed like it was
just an opinion and not a fact.
Really. You should donate your
brain to science or something.
you're curious about the
protests that occurred 45 years ago.
I'm not sure what more I can
tell you about it, to be honest.
Eventually, he was found guilty
and expelled from the school.
Somebody else was actually
running the show behind the scenes.
I drew up an outline and a
schedule for writing the anthology.
I thought everyone would have
forgotten about it by this point.
Most people call the cultural
festival Kanyasai, but you don't.
And why was it so important to
you that I get involved with it?
Ten years from now, how will I
feel when I look back at my life?
But only the person who wrote
it knows for sure which one it is.
You know, I'd always hoped I'd
be able to see him again someday.
Pathetic as it sounds, we were
all too afraid of being punished.
I went to my uncle, and asked
if he'd tell me what Hyouka meant.
I'm sure it had something to do
with what you said to me before.
if we were going to solve the
mystery before my uncle's funeral.
He left school as a martyr for
what he thought was a noble cause.
I think we should've given more
weight to what it said in Hyouka.
But what I don't understand is
why anyone is asking about it now.
I'm sure he'll tell you all about
it if you don't mind listening.
As a matter of fact, we banned
that name in the Classic Lit Club.
There are some gaps in the story,
but I think we can fill them in.
Now, then, you said there was
something you wanted to ask me about.
I suggested that you ask Satoshi
and Ibara to help you out with it.
I wouldn't expect you to put effort
into solving a mystery like this.
The best that we're going to be
able to do is make an educated guess.
Whether he volunteered himself as
a sacrifice for the other students?
I don't know anyone in this world
less energy efficient than Chitanda.
I seriously doubt that we'd all be
here asking you about it right now.
I'd say it was more like someone
had threatened to take away our toys,
Mm-hmm. We all have to meet up in
the clubroom to talk about something.
Those kids weren't afraid to stand
up for what they really cared about.
Are you starting to see that living
a sunny life isn't so bad after all?
Everyone was afraid that meant the
cultural festival would be abolished.
The story we just heard makes it
clear what the anthology's title means.
We'd whipped ourselves into a
self-righteous frenzy as only the young can.
Can you really call it "accepting"
if somebody forces you to do something?
Whether or not things change as time
passes, what I'm feeling now is real.
Yeah. She said that when she was a
second-year, she was the club president.
The administration would give in to
us eventually, but we didn't know that.
I mean either we went off in the wrong
direction or we didn't go far enough.
Jun Sekitani wanted to leave an enduring
message about what happened to him,
it means that our Kanyasai came at the
cost of somebody's high school career.
holding his head high as he knowingly
sacrificed his whole high school career
We've got to put Mr. Lazy Bones to
work somehow, and this is our best chance.
In addition to all the rallies and
speeches, students were boycotting classes.
The years passed, and sure enough, the
cultural festival was shortened anyway,
The combat sports building is by far
the oldest facility we have at Kami High.
The responsibility for unraveling that
mystery was split between the four of us.
Did you know somehow that it would force
me to reconsider my priorities in life?
Did Jun Sekitani willingly take the hit
for the other students who were involved?
I know it's possible that 10 years from
now, I won't care so much about all this.
Like I've said before, I'm not doing
anything special. It's just luck, that's all.
And you put together this theory from
nothing more than the material you have here?
The drawing on the anthology's cover is
supposed to symbolize what happened, right?
Instead, you locked yourself in the
bathroom until you could come up with an answer.
Hotaro seems to think that something about
his theory is either wrong or incomplete.
"We can't content ourselves with being a
small-time school in a sleepy little town."
They took "Sekitani-sai" and switched the
reading to make it "Kanyasai" to honor Jun.
If he's still alive, does Jun Sekitani
have any regrets about his time in high school?
To be kicked out of school over a festival
and have a whole phase of his life altered?
How many people could sacrifice everything
and not feel a bit of resentment or regret?
Forty-five years ago she was a first-year
in high school, so today she'd be around 60.
that building was still new enough that it
didn't need to be fixed up like the others.
It clearly states in the foreword that Jun
Sekitani's story is in no way a heroic tale.
Do you have any idea why my uncle chose
Hyouka to be the title of the club's anthology?
Funny thing is, it's not even the first
mystery you've solved since high school started.
And let's not forget how she reacted when
she found out we were in the Classic Lit Club.
If you'd said "I've got no clue" and left it
at that, I doubt anyone would've blamed you.
"This has been a lot of fun, and I know I'll
look back in 10 years and be glad I did it."
In those years, it was almost as if students
were channeling the nation's restless energy
It wasn't, but the principal did inform us
that the festival would last for only two days,
Something tells me if people knew that, they
probably wouldn't even use the term Kanyasai.
Does being more passionate about stuff make
life more exciting or just more heartbreaking?
Instead, they settled for making an example
of the movement's nominal leader, Jun Sekitani.
You didn't seem to like the idea much at
first, so what made you change your mind about it?
Oreki pieced together some information and
came up with a possible outline of what went down
Being a club president, taking midterms,
writing an anthology, solving riddles from the past?
At any rate, we formed a sort of coalition to
protest the shortening of the cultural festival.
I don't really think you would call a meeting
like this unless something important was going on.
I mean, I've been working with her this whole
time and the name thing never even occurred to me.
Well, that's the end of my story, unless you
have any other questions that you'd like to ask me.
Sure, it's possible that Miss Itoigawa is who
we're looking for, but do you have any solid proof?
And she looks around 60, which is just about how
old the foreword's author would be at this point.
There are still a few tiny holes in our theory
about Chitanda's uncle, and I'm trying to close them.
But having your high-school experience cut short
because you and your friends wanted a longer festival?
Since almost all the students were involved with
the movement, they couldn't very well punish everyone.
And that's why you assume his expulsion was delayed
until October; they wanted to let the tension die down?
could you do me a favor and
confirm for my fellow club
members here that your maiden
name is, in fact, Yoko Koriyama?