Yes.
Psh.
Yeah.
Okay.
What?
Hotaro!
Well...
Dammit!
Nothing.
Yeah, hi.
The setup.
Let's see.
However...
Next time:
Hey, there.
Fine, then!
What is it?
But still...
And, well...
Irisu, look.
Interesting.
So listen...
It had to be!
Meaning what?
That's right.
You're right.
A Tarot book?
"The Empress.
Please enjoy!
What's wrong?
By the way...
Yeah, she did.
Listen, Oreki.
Okay, my turn.
It's pathetic.
Am I mistaken?
Where's Mayaka?
I'm not coming.
Of course I do.
The truth is...
At first glance,
And that's that.
Hold on a second!
Nice people, huh?
Quite impressive.
Isn't that right?
Well, yeah, but...
Hey, what's wrong?
You can be honest.
Who cares, anyway?
But I gotta say...
Whoa, are you okay?
Sounds about right.
You're lying to me!
Right. So what's up?
It was Hongo's idea.
Oh, great. You, too?
The theatre setting.
The gruesome murder.
Interesting, indeed.
Sherlock Holmes did.
Yes, that's correct.
Hotaro! Hey, wait up!
Here's my hypothesis.
Why would he do that?
Oh, yeah, I get that.
then I'll let this go.
So you didn't like it?
Oh, right, I remember!
That is just like you.
Sherlock Holmes, right?
to be perfectly honest.
The cast of characters.
So Ibara was "Justice."
What gave my plot away?
That was just a tactic.
See you tomorrow, Oreki.
It's pretty fascinating.
Change my point of view?
No, I don't mind at all.
But in the film he does.
I have no hard evidence.
It makes more sense now.
There's no inconsistency.
No, it's not that at all.
But where did I go wrong?
Yeah, I guess that's true.
From what Satoshi told me,
Ibara mentioned that, too.
There was a narrator, too.
Satoshi was "The Magician."
One green tea for the lady.
What are you talking about?
She had to go to Manga Club.
She would have been furious!
What does that say about me?
No lucky flashes of insight.
Yep, that's not too far off.
And Chitanda was "The Fool."
It's about the film's ending.
It's still pretty early, huh?
It was that great of an idea.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Pathetic. Some detective I am.
They already wrapped the film.
I'd like to discuss something.
Huh? No, it's not that at all.
That's telling, and here's why.
Now, I don't know Hongo at all.
That's what I have to find out!
"Curiosity, impulse to action."
I dunno, maybe I am "Strength."
Just what did you mean by that?
even in the unfinished version.
Did Chitanda have to leave, too?
I gotta go. I'll see you around.
That's why you came to watch it.
I can't wrap my brain around it.
That would be just like Satoshi.
So what did you want to discuss?
Wasn't that your plan all along?
Huh? But I thought the window...
chased Kaito, and sliced him up.
What would make you think I did?
well, that's the only reason why.
One Yunnan tea for the gentleman.
Yeah, they turned up in the film,
I really thought it was fantastic.
Is that what you actually believe?
how Hongo wanted the movie to end.
But unfortunately, I was mistaken.
But some joker still voted for it.
Not like myself? What's that mean?
"Those Things Piled Up Endlessly."
Did I ignore it? Not intentionally.
Why would Satoshi pick this for me?
Is there something wrong with that?
No, it's not like me. You're right.
Ugh, your guess is as good as mine.
Yeah, it's nothing. What's going on?
Then what were you so curious about?
And it would have been a lot easier.
"Equality, righteousness, fairness."
I copied a few of them down for you.
Oh, right, that makes perfect sense!
If I tell you, promise not to laugh!
Good, I'm actually glad it's just us.
I have to tell you that you're wrong.
I don't think it was what she wanted.
I didn't know Sis was into this stuff.
First, the small amount of blood used.
And that arm was remarkably well-made.
I'm not sure why, but that's a relief.
Please tell me. I have to know, Oreki!
in preparation for writing this script?
You said something else to me before...
Well, why don't I just ask, like usual?
but I don't think that's the case here.
Was the plot twist part of Hongo's plan?
And if she was too frail to handle that,
So, as far as the answers are concerned,
Well, I'd better get going to Manga Club.
That's all I wanted to talk to you about.
In the ones marked with an "X," they die.
and she couldn't claim that you hurt her.
I don't dispute any of these accusations.
Well, I was not being completely sincere.
So that's how she wanted the story to go?
How could I have forgotten about the rope?
Are you basing that on something specific?
This is about Class 2-F's movie, isn't it?
I'm beginning to think you guys are right.
And what makes you say that, specifically?
That's an option I've considered, as well.
"Inner fortitude, fighting spirit, bonds?"
What? No, I didn't know anything about it.
So what about this other single vote, here?
Then, you replaced her script with my work,
So what, then? This isn't like you, y'know.
There are two, but it doesn't matter which.
Oh, I wanted to talk to you about something.
Chitanda was actually concerned about Hongo.
How were you able to get your hands on this?
From here out, my statements are conjecture.
She was much too timid to speak up that way.
Unless Hongo talks, we might never find out.
Hell, maybe she even saw one used in a movie!
The killer... lurks among you all undetected!
Listen, there's a launch party this Saturday.
are the ones in which the characters survive.
All I had to do was ask if I could borrow it.
She just couldn't stomach it when people died.
"Initiative, originality," and "interest," huh?
It's not like he could change my point of view.
Konosu snuck in using the rope Hongo asked for,
or what made him decide to forgive her, either.
and the end caught everyone totally by surprise.
Or did you come up with all of that on your own?
I thought you would've already gone home by now.
There's something I wanted to talk to you about.
Satoshi and Ibara already talked to me about it.
No way, I am not controlled by women in any way!
We couldn't have done it without you, so thanks.
A lone vote for having zero murders in the film.
And that was how Hongo cast her vote, wasn't it?
Just one strike, though, not enough to kill him.
The injury could be accounted for pretty easily,
which wasn't until the mid-1920s at the earliest.
Maybe I'll read a book to take my mind off of it.
Maternal affection, a fertile mind, sensitivity."
What the heck? That doesn't sound like me at all!
'Cause there are only about 30 kids in the class.
I heard that Hongo didn't even come to the shoot.
and demand the class reshoot without the changes.
Have you ever heard of the term "narrative trick"?
They said they knew it wasn't what Hongo intended.
I wasn't asked to come on board as a screenwriter.
All that really matters to you is the bottom line.
I mean the window in the stage right sitting room.
Was your empathy for Hongo really the only reason?
Do you wanna take a walk with me down by the river?
If you've got something in mind, you should say it.
Maybe she didn't have confidence in her conclusion.
I wasn't your detective. I was your mystery writer.
Do you care if I spoil some of his stories for you?
But in reality it was just a scriptwriting contest.
But if you're trying to pass it off as Hongo's work,
If it is, and you feel like you made the right call,
If the ending you wrote is the one she came up with,
So if it seems to you like I didn't enjoy the movie,
The last scene was really quite a shock to everyone!
Second, the unexpected outcome of the questionnaire.
Regardless, I have no choice but to say this to you:
But you decided to take matters into your own hands.
Ah, that must be why Hongo wished Konosu luck, then.
The cast didn't just consist of the people onscreen.
Wow, this is a lot more embarrassing than I thought.
She preferred happy endings to tragedies. That's all.
That's because you had manipulated our point of view.
You're not acting quite like yourself, either, Oreki.
Why would she do that if it wasn't a part of her plan?
Did I twist the narrative to make it fit Kaito better?
But the other kids in the class seem like nice people.
The class film turned out quite well, don't you think?
But Kaito died, any way you slice it, no pun intended.
Hongo didn't have the nerve to stand up for her script
I'm sorry, I guess I could be mistaken about that part.
And Hongo still would have been able to rest, you mean?
It's ironic that you don't know. I was talking about...
Why didn't Irisu talk to someone who was close to Hongo?
She couldn't substantially prove you did anything wrong!
What makes you think the rope was even part of the setup?
Personally, the movie turned out to be right up my alley.
I'm not saying that you did anything wrong at all, Oreki.
From what I've seen, that doesn't seem like Irisu at all.
and met up with the rest of the cast, looking nonchalant.
which is kind of out of character for you, so I wondered.
I did a great job if my assignment was to screw things up.
Not my sister, Chitanda, Irisu, or any of the rest of 'em.
Do you think you can come? We'd all love to see you there.
staging a hundred murders in the film would be impossible.
Normally, I'd say "to stop the murderer from getting him,"
The rope didn't figure into
your new conclusion in any way!
And if it was all your idea,
I promise not to say anything!
all those screams of frustration
were hidden in the script!
Her impulsive classmates
decided to improvise the violence.
Is that what's twirling around
inside your head over there?
Exactly, she didn't read
anything other than Sherlock Holmes.
And she probably wouldn't have
escorted us to the detectives.
While I was busy trying to
figure out the puzzle of the film,
because of the glass that was
all over the floor in the room.
I think that Hongo and I are
really similar in a lot of ways.
It was clever to have the camera
man be the seventh character.
I was actually more interested
in Hongo as a person, you know?
No matter how hard I think
about it, it won't change anything.
We don't have some comprehensive
list of everything she's read!
Dwelling on it now is just a
waste of time and precious energy.
Hongo wasn't thinking about the
plotlines when she marked them.
But it wasn't keeping in line
with the story she wanted to tell.
Isn't that a way of fooling the
reader with clever storytelling?
Doyle didn't use narrative tricks
in the Sherlock Holmes novels.
The way things were going, Hongo
was becoming the class villain.
Knowing Kaito's supposed to live
solves the locked-room problem.
Konosu is the real attacker,
and the entry point was the window.
Anyway, I thought your idea
turned out to be really entertaining,
And if you choose to call it an
outright lie, that's your choice.
You weren't convinced by any of
the other detectives' hypotheses,
Then she climbed back up to the
second floor, using the same rope,
I bet that after Konosu cuts
Kaito, she stays around for a minute,
makes his way to the stage left
wing, and collapses to the ground.
But I find it hard to believe
she'd be on par with Agatha Christie!
and Kaito asks her why she stabbed
him, because he's baffled by it.
How I was gonna tie up all the
loose ends and wrap the movie, right?
Is he using the Tarot to hint at
some kind of judgment he has of me?
They did? Only the original six
showed up in the version that I saw.
I found some notes tucked into the
novels that Hongo read to prepare.
She didn't want anyone to have to
die in the script she wrote at all.
Eba knows Hongo really well, so
she could have helped Irisu figure out
But wait... What about the seventh
character Hongo was trying to cast?
Hongo insisted they find a rope
that could hold a person's full weight!
Why? Do you not want them to overhear
what you need to discuss with me?
I thought the whole script thing
was really bizarre from the beginning.
No, I didn't really have any interest
in how the movie was going to end,
Then, to cover for her, for whatever
reason, he sends her back upstairs,
I would be lying to you if I said I
believed the ending was Hongo's idea.
I don't know what she intended to
write, but I am positive that wasn't it.
But I don't think she came up with
something that good, so she kept quiet.
So why was the door to the room the
other six found Kaito in locked, then?
Yeah, but we still don't know why
Konosu stabbed Kaito in the first place,
and why would the one who was stabbed
let their attacker get away with it?
I don't handle it very well when
characters have to die in movies, either.
You just have to know what kind of
script Hongo actually intended to write.
But then, how would he explain away
the fact that he's been cut that badly?
It's nothing major, but I would prefer
to talk about it with you in private.
You set her up to come down with an
illness and leave her script unfinished.
That's why I told you that the idea
you came up with was such a brilliant one.
I assumed she had just written them
down as ideas she might use in her script.
He could just say that he fell on a
piece of the broken glass and cut himself.
Once I thought of it in those terms,
several puzzles suddenly made sense to me.
No one caught on to the fact that they
were doing your dirty work, not even me!
When you told me I was special, was
that just so you could manipulate me, too?!
Kaito went into the stage left wing by
himself, and locked the door behind him.
I'm sure she would have had enough
confidence in it to share it with the others.
Are you implying that Hongo still wanted
to write the rest of the script herself?
I don't think they would be disrespectful
of her idea, or insult her or anything.
The strangest part is that the script
never says that Kaito dies from his injury.
Did you happen to know more about this
incident than what you're letting on here?
The version that we ended up with didn't
have any of her real feelings left in it.
I saw the script as a literary problem,
and forgot about the human side of things.
I talked it over with Satoshi, and I
realized that the stories with double circles
I'm curious. What kind of script did
Hongo originally dream up for the class film?
I'm dying to know why Hongo was trying
to depict that scenario in the first place.
Maybe she learned to use narrative tricks
by reading about them in some other book!
You don't truly care about the feelings
of people who don't have natural abilities.
How could I have missed an inconsistency
so glaring that two people picked up on it?
Then you rallied her classmates together
and held a meeting of collective deduction.
And if all that's true, what was it that
pushed her to the point of not finishing it?
Once you realized they couldn't write to
your standards, you dragged us into it, too.
I just thought it didn't fit with the rest
of the film, if you want my honest opinion.
Do you remember our conversation about the
books Hongo used to study the mystery genre
"The Red-Haired League" and "The Three
Garridebs" have pretty much the same plot line.
I think she had some guilt about ignoring
the death toll tally from the questionnaire.
I would think Eba would have gotten so mad
at the class she wouldn't have participated.
Did Hongo really not tell anyone else in
the class how the rest of her film played out?
Even if she had gotten sick in the middle
of things, they could have asked her about it.
The surprise twist of the murderer being the
camera man in this film is a perfect example.
No. From the way Eba described her, I get
the impression Hongo's too meek to insist on it.
I don't think that kind of girl would have
the gall to keep her classmates waiting around.
I guess we'll leave it at that, but why would
anyone want to stab one of their classmates,
Except for a handful of cases, narrative
tricks weren't in use until Agatha Christie's era,
I think Hongo had a clear vision of her script
from the beginning, right up to the very end.
"Strength is represented by a picture of a
ferocious lion being controlled by a kind woman."
Oh, I just had the realization that I understand
Hongo's intentions a little bit better now.
Do you remember the last time we were here,
when you said that I was gifted, a "true genius?"
So, Oreki, do you know what it was that made me
so curious about all of this in the first place?
That when people have talent and can't recognize
it, they unknowingly hurt those who don't have any.
It may not have been what Hongo originally intended,
but at the end of the day it was a great ending.
I believe that all of her regrets, how she really
felt about not being able to finish what she started,
I never even considered that Hongo could have
written her feelings into the script as some hidden code.
And I thought the scene where the other six looked
into the camera at the same time had a lot of impact.
When you said it's right to acknowledge who you really
are, you were thinking of your own selfish interests!
So why did she mark, "The Red-Haired League" with a
triangle, but "The Three Garridebs" with a double-circle?