Wow. Looks like Sho made the finals.
Yeah. That's what it says.
Mm-hm!
He's amazing.
Seeing something like that makes me wonder
if I have any natural talents, but I doubt it.
I'm pretty sure the gifted genes skipped right over me.
I keep trying to tell myself I'm just a late bloomer.
That's only wishful thinking, though.
Come on, what do ya mean? You're a human database.
Yeah, I am quite proud of that
trait: my ability to store information.
But even if I put effort into developing
it, I'll never be a quiz show king.
Really?
Heck no. And I resent it.
I envy people like Sho.
Being a talented genius has its disadvantages, too.
Yeah, like what?
Extraordinary people don't even have the option to
lead a normal, boring existence like the rest of us do.
Uh...
Hold on.
You think a mundane life is better somehow?
You would think that.
You're such a weirdo.
Mm...
I wonder if you'll actually be able to live a normal life.
What is that supposed to mean?
Look, I've accepted that I don't have any special talents.
I think the jury is still out on you, though,
so I'm gonna hold off on making
a determination a bit longer.
If you think I could live an extraordinary life,
I have to question your powers of observation.
Hey, I'm still gathering evidence. Gimme a break here.
Anyway...
We should probably hurry along to the meeting.
Mayaka will have both our hides if we show up late again.
That's for sure.
It's summer vacation, for crying out loud.
You're late!
Ah...!
Yeah, laugh it up.
You two are in deep trouble.
Where's Chitanda?
Oh. She hasn't shown up yet either.
I'm a little worried.
That's a pretty stark disparity.
There's a disparity in your behavior.
I'm so sorry I'm late!
There's a film screening!
You guys!
Do you wanna see a student film?
Class 2-F produced a movie, and they're
gonna be showing it in a few minutes!
Hm?
I have a friend who's in that class,
and we were just talking about it.
That's actually why I was late.
She wants some outside input on the
film, so she asked if we would watch it.
What kind of movie is it?
Um, she said it was a murder mystery.
Oh, yeah?
Well, that's right up our alley.
I think this is the place.
We decided to take you up on your invitation.
Well, I'm happy to hear that.
Thanks for coming.
I appreciate you taking the time to help us out with this.
This is Mayaka Ibara.
That's Satoshi Fukube.
And he's Hotaro Oreki.
We're all in the Classic Lit Club
together, as I mentioned earlier.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Fuyumi Irisu.
Oh! Now I remember.
You and I have met before.
I thought you looked familiar. I was right!
Uh, I don't remember you.
Sorry about that.
Oh, we were both on the cultural
festival planning committee.
We mediated that dispute between the
Light Music Club and the Drama Club?
Talk about drama!
I've never seen Satoshi so eager to please.
Yeah, sorry, still doesn't ring a bell.
U-Uh... No worries.
Hey, Chi, how do you know this girl?
My family and the Irisu family
have been close for generations.
I've know her for as long as I can remember.
Being old money sure seems like a lot of work.
Anyway... Here is a copy of the movie
the other kids in my class produced.
I'd be grateful if you would watch it
and tell me your honest opinions of it.
Sure, we can't wait!
So all we have to do is watch
it and tell you what we think?
Yes, is that strange to you?
Well, if we don't like it, does that mean
you're going to reshoot the parts we criticize,
or are you just showing us for some free publicity?
Neither.
Then I don't understand what
you gain from showing it to us.
You bring up a legitimate point.
The purpose involves your opinions,
but it's not about the quality, per se.
I just think it's more efficient to show
you the film before explaining further.
So?
I guess I'll wait and see.
Our movie doesn't have an official title yet,
but the working title is "Mystery."
Once the film is over, I'll be asking you
specific questions, so please pay attention.
All right. Let's get things started.
I'll be back in a bit. Happy hunting.
"Hunting?"
These students from Class 2-F have
decided to participate in the Kanyasai.
They need supplies from the Narakubo area for
their exhibit and are now heading to the site.
How much farther is it?
Not much farther. We should be there in five more minutes.
You said the same thing five minutes ago!
This is pretty tough going.
I'm hot, and I'm starting to feel tired and hungry.
You're not the only one who is hot and tired!
Now! We gotta keep marching!
About what I'd expect from a student film.
Mm-hm. Yes, I see it.
That's Narakubo over there.
So awesome.
You're right.
I think it was worth the trek to get supplies.
All that aside, it would be wise to find a place
to camp for the night before hunting for materials!
You're right.
That looks like a good place, over there, doesn't it?
Let's go see!
I dunno, guys.
I have a bad feeling about this.
A haunted theater!
A haunted theater?
It's so dusty.
The roof seems like it's holding up okay, though.
It's too dangerous to sleep in this room.
There's glass scattered about!
We need to find somewhere to camp before it gets dark out.
I think I found a floorplan over here.
Oh! It is a floorplan!
Let's split up and explore the building!
Hey! That sounds dangerous!
And I am certain all the doors in here are locked!
There has to be a set of keys
lying around this place somewhere.
What is that? An office?
What do you think those keys are for?
I think those are the master keys.
We should leave them here.
It would be bad if they got lost.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
We found keys.
They should unlock all the rooms in the house.
Okay, let's split up and see what we can find.
Right.
If this were reality,
there's no way they'd all split up, you know what I mean?
What are you getting at?
Something's about to happen. I can feel it... can't you?
What?
He was the one talking to me!
The incident occurred soon after.
See, I told you so!
Hm?
Did you find anything?
There are pieces of broken mirror everywhere.
We can't use any of the rooms I've seen.
None of the rooms that I saw would work, either.
Hey, Sugimura!
What did you find up there?
Well, it's pretty clean, mostly.
The rooms in this wing...
...might be our best options.
Hey, where's Kaito?
He must still be lookin' around.
Let's go find him.
Maybe he found something worth seeing.
Is this a sitting room?
No Kaito here.
Hm? Not in here, either.
Farther down, maybe?
This one's locked.
It won't budge. That's kinda weird.
What should we do?
I'll go get the master keys.
Yeah, I'll come with you.
Kaito!
Th-There's blood everywhere!
Oh, no. What is that?
I'm amazed she can buy into this nonsense.
Damn it! He's dead!
Oh, no.
Um... Is that it?
But, wait.
There's no way that's the ending!
That's all we have so far.
So, what's the point of this screening?
I'd like to know who you all
think is the culprit in the film.
I will explain the whole thing in a moment,
but first, I want to hear each of your opinions.
Technically speaking,
what would be your impressions of our film?
Well, if I could be perfectly honest,
I think it's a bit clumsy.
I agree with that assessment.
No matter how much passion goes into a
film, without real skill, it feels amateur.
But isn't that okay?
I mean it is an amateur film.
Yes. I think it's fine enough work for what it is.
A student film should get some leeway
to be a bit self-indulgent, right?
Mm-hm.
Let's not get bogged down discussing aesthetics.
I was just curious.
What's the most obvious issue
with the project, as it stands?
The fact that it's nowhere near finished?
Yes.
Even if it's not perfect, we have to complete it.
The crew shot at a unique location,
and we were only able to do so during the
summer break, which has proven to be problematic.
Why do you say that? Did the shoot not go as scheduled?
The actual shoot went according to plan.
We were supposed to wrap everything
up right on time, next Sunday.
Okay, so what's the problem, then?
The script's not done.
Mayu Hongo has written manga,
which is more experience than anyone else in
class, so she agreed to write the hour-long screen play.
That's a tall order!
She did pretty well with it, overall.
But when she reached the point that you saw in
the film, she got very sick and couldn't finish.
Wait a minute.
Do you expect us to take over?
I could never ask anything like that of you.
Now then, getting back to my earlier question.
Who do you think committed the murder?
Hongo got sick just as we were getting to the resolution.
I think that someone who watched the film up to
this point should be able to deduce who did it.
But are there really going to be enough clues to
figure that out in a screenplay by a novice writer?
I believe there should be.
Hongo immersed herself and
focused mostly on Sherlock Holmes.
She followed the Ten Commandments,
Nine Propositions, and the Twenty Rules.
Oh, yeah?
What, like from the Bible?
No, Knox's Ten Commandments.
Those, plus the Nine Propositions and Twenty
Rules dictate what makes a good detective story.
Correct.
They say the keys to solving the crime
must always be presented fairly to the reader.
So, with that in mind, who do you
think is the culprit in this case?
That's what she meant by, "Happy hunting."
I'm not very good with that kind of question.
I store information. I don't know how to interpret it.
Me, either.
I don't pay much attention to details.
Though, I suspect there's someone here who does.
Hm?
Don't look at me.
Why not?
This is right up your alley, isn't it?
You are the star detective of
the Classic Lit Club, after all.
C'mon, why the sour face?
I wasn't watching with that in mind.
In that case, let's ask her to show us the movie again.
What? Give me a break!
There's no need to overthink it.
I just want an outside opinion.
Oh, is that right?
Well, then I think Yamanishi is the murderer for sure.
What makes you say that?
'Cause I don't like her crappy attitude.
Oreki! Don't play around!
Hey, Irisu, why don't you try
to figure out who the murderer is?
I don't have any experience with mysteries.
No?
Well, if that's the case, then why'd you let
the class choose it as the genre for your project?
I wasn't attached to the film yet
when they were making those decisions.
I got back from my family vacation to Hokkaido,
and the film was already in this sticky predicament.
I jumped in the day before yesterday to sort it out.
If I'd been involved, I doubt it would have moved forward.
One more question.
Why did you call on the Classic Lit
Club to help you out with this issue?
Well, first, I knew Chitanda would have my back on this.
And secondly, I heard all about the Hyouka business.
Huh?
I didn't think anyone else knew about that.
Did Miss Itoigawa tell her?
When I agreed to help my classmates out of
this mess, I remembered what I'd heard about you.
I thought that perhaps I could enlist you as
my detectives and solve the problem even faster.
Well, don't expect us to do all the work.
Not at all.
I sincerely apologize if I gave you that impression.
Please forgive me.
So, that's the end of this morning's screening.
Well, then. Thanks for coming.
Hey! Please, wait a minute!
What's going to happen with the end of the movie, then?
I don't know.
We'll do our best with what we have.
But I am bracing for the possibility that we won't finish.
We can't let that happen.
I would be heartbroken to know
all their hard work was done in vain!
I just don't think I could bear it!
What's it to her?
Irisu should be upset.
Yeah.
It would be frustrating to leave it unfinished like that!
I agree.
You all came together as a team to get it done.
And also, Hongo worked herself to
the point of illness for this project!
Why would she go to such great
lengths just to give up halfway through?
I just... I have to know!
Let's help them out, Hotaro. Why not?
Got something better to do?
We must do this, Oreki.
Let's avenge Hongo's death and solve this crime!
Hongo isn't dead. She's sick.
Ah! Oh, that's right.
We have to help them, Oreki!
What happens if we do decide to help, but we
can't figure out who the murderer is either?
Are we supposed to just bow down
and beg for forgiveness from Class 2-F?
I don't want that kind of responsibility.
I'll make you a deal.
How about you act as observers, rather than detectives?
Observers?
Uh...
You'd listen to the opinions of
our class's appointed detectives,
then offer your viewpoints,
and that'd be the extent of it.
Well?
That sounds okay. Deal.
Thanks so much. I appreciate it.
Irisu's family is pretty famous.
That's the reason right over there.
The Irisus have run the general hospital for decades now.
Oh, so she's the heiress to a giant medical fortune.
Yeah, but that's not the only reason
Irisu, herself, is well-known around here.
People at school have given her a nickname.
Do you know what they call her?
No idea.
"The Empress."
Why... does she rule people?
Ugh, she's not a dominatrix.
I set it up, you knocked it down.
I salute you.
What are you doing?
Well, she's pretty, but that's not the whole reason.
I've heard she can get anyone to do her bidding.
People are drawn to her, and before they know it,
she's manipulated them into being her pawns.
What? Well, that's not creepy at all.
Maybe, but I have to say,
the Empress was generous enough
to grant us an audience with her.
We might do well to adopt our own symbols in her honor.
What do you mean?
Mayaka should be... "Justice."
It's between that and "Judgement."
I don't get it.
Symbols from the Tarot deck.
Huh.
Well, Fuku, what would you be?
"The Fool," I think.
Nah, "The Magician" is better.
I think Chitanda should be "The Fool."
Yeah, you're right.
"The Fool" really does suit me, now that you mention it.
Impulsiveness is definitely
one of my shortcomings, after all.
I'm lost.
Yeah, same.
What about Oreki?
That's a no-brainer. He'd be "Strength."
Huh? Seriously?
If I had to pick, I would label him "The Star," instead.
Nope. This guy's Strength, for sure.
It's perfect for him.
Hmph. I have a suspicion that's not a compliment.
That's a fair assessment.
You're a total jerk.
Not a chance.
Yeah?
Well, good morning, Oreki.
I thought we could walk together.
Does she have to be so polite all the time?
Good morning, everyone!
Morning.
Mornin'!
I'm excited that we get to meet the detectives today.
I'm looking forward to listening to
their hypotheses about the murderer.
When did you have time to make this happen?
Over chat.
Kamiyama High School has a private online chat
room that only the students are allowed to use.
Wow! I didn't know that!
You'll have to show me!
Yeah, that sounds fun!
Yes? Come on in!
Is this the Classic Lit Club room?
It is.
Are you the girl who Irisu sent from Class 2-F?
That's right. My name is Eba.
It's very nice to meet you all.
I believe I'm supposed to take you to meet our detectives?
Irisu told me she had briefed you on the film situation.
All right, follow me.
Chi, did you bring snacks today?
Yep!
I brought these fancy chocolates
someone sent to our house.
I thought that it would be nice to share
them with everyone while we were working today!
Sounds great!
I mean, after all, it's so much harder to
think clearly when you're hungry, ya know?
Man, I can't wait to hear the
detectives' theories about the film!
Aren't you so excited, Hotaro?
I'm glad you're all having such a good time.
Hey, Eba! I have a question for ya.
Go ahead.
Who are these detectives, anyway?
The assistant director, the props master, and the PR girl.
Cool!
So what exactly is your
involvement in the filmmaking process?
I don't have anything to do with it, as a matter of fact.
To be honest, I wasn't interested.
Well how about that? A girl after my own heart.
Eba, if you don't mind my
asking, were you and Hongo close?
Why do you ask?
Oh.
I was just curious about the kind of person who
would be able to write a murder mystery script like this.
If I had to describe her,
I'd say...
She's a no-nonsense, meticulous person,
really responsible, kind to a fault, and fragile.
She's one of my best friends.
Interesting.
Here we are.
The film is on hiatus right now,
so I doubt anyone else is gonna show up.
You shouldn't be interrupted.
Everyone, I'd like you to meet our detectives.
Next time:
"The Case of the Furuoka Deserted Village Murder."