Hm.
Oh.
Hm?
Mm.
Huh?
I...
Sure!
Sure.
Here.
Phew!
Ahem.
Ahem!
Uh...
Yeah.
Boom!
Uh...
Ha...
Yeah.
Well,
Hmph.
Uh...
Yeah.
Ahem.
Whoa!
Uh...
Ciao!
Yeah.
Huh...
Dunno.
Right?
Hello?
Later.
Hello.
Well...
I know!
Hold on.
Uh, why?
I dunno.
Why not?
Totally.
You know,
You know.
Rejected.
Um, what?
You okay?
You know.
I buy it.
Good call.
Hey there.
Now, then.
Some rope?
Very well.
So anyway.
Like what?
Next time:
Ciao, ciao!
Yeah. Sure.
Uh... Sure.
Okay, then.
The window?
Well, uh...
She saw it.
Is that so?
What is it?
Well, gosh.
Just think:
What is it?
Not really.
Why's that?
All righty.
Well, Oreki?
Tipsy, much?
"On the fly"?
Say what now?
What is this?
Let me think.
What are they?
That's strong!
Well, maybe...
Oh. I'm sorry.
I just mean...
Yeah. I guess.
Haba's theory!
Mystery solved.
Really? "Boom"?
Well, anyway...
I mean, "ciao"!
Phantom killer?
Rejected again.
Even on the fly.
And you, Mayaka?
See what I mean?
But not for you.
This is the key.
I'll bet you do.
The props master.
Nice to meet you.
Of course it was!
No, none of them.
What do you mean?
Don't you get it?
I get your point.
You may be right.
A good deduction.
Yeah, 'bout what?
How could it not?
Sorry, am I late?
Great, thank you!
What do you mean?
Hope it goes well.
Sure. It's simple.
How do you figure?
Feasible and lame.
The classics, huh?
I don't read them.
I just don't know.
Good story, right?
I have to admit...
Finally, we have...
More than anything.
Through the window.
Sawakiguchi, right?
As for the title...
So, what's the deal?
Oh, I almost forgot!
I think it was June.
I wouldn't say that.
Why do you say that?
That guy's attitude.
Can I have one, too?
Come on. Let us see.
I've been wondering.
Yeah, I know, right?
"Blind Spot to All."
This is Junya Nakajo.
Well. Questions over?
A locked-room murder.
Thanks! See ya later!
You think he's right?
Hey, that looks cool!
Hey! Can you hear me?
I think she's asleep.
I'm sorry about this.
Significant, like how?
So there ya go, right?
Seriously? Not at all?
Voted by the majority.
So, what do you think?
I mean, why would they?
In the stage left wing.
Can anyone tell us why?
"The Unseen Incursion."
Pretty great, actually.
No, I think he's wrong.
That would pretty dumb.
It's wrong. Just wrong!
One prop in particular.
Well, wanna get started?
I'm not being defensive.
So, as Nakajo suggested,
Very well. I understand.
There's one other thing.
So, other possibilities.
Oh, I feel totally fine.
How did it go this time?
And that's Tomohiro Haba.
This is gonna be awesome!
There. Let's take a look.
The window's here, right?
What about you, Chitanda?
It may take me some time.
Hey, Oreki, look at this.
How are you feeling, Chi?
That part's solid enough.
I'm just fine, thank you.
Have fun! We'll talk soon!
No need for a door at all.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Did the interview go well?
Hello, there, Sawakiguchi!
Nope. She was recommended.
"Bloody Beast" would work.
Misaki Sawakiguchi. PR rep.
Oh, me? Ah. Well, you know.
I'll see if I can find one.
A floorplan from town hall.
and being seen by somebody.
That's it! Now I'm grouchy!
Oh. I see. The window, huh?
Gettin' a little worked up.
Kinda depressing, isn't it?
He's our assistant director.
so thanks a lot for helping.
Was it pretty well-received?
Okay then, who's the killer?
The grass was way overgrown.
Wait a sec! It's summer now!
Would you care to elaborate?
You really think that's all?
What other props were there?
If not, I'll just be goin...
She didn't skimp on details.
You sound a little defensive.
I'm sorry. Did I hit a nerve?
Well, that's my take, anyway.
Let's start with... this guy!
All they want is a good story.
I say play the title straight.
That's the real question here.
Now you're grasping at straws.
It's not much of a plot twist.
It doesn't sit right with you?
There's no way for us to know.
what kind does everybody read?
This is your specialty, right?
Whoops! Did I eat all of them?
so it must've been shut tight.
There's still one person left.
And making the film a mystery?
I don't think so. I'm curious!
Except those are horror films.
So how did the killer get out?
Whiskey-filled chocolates, huh?
Why would it be "well-crafted"?
I'd say that's highly unlikely.
"Murder on the Orient Express"?
What's wrong is wrong. The end!
No one had any problems with it.
"That's him! He's the murderer!"
Satoshi, you have the floorplan?
Come on. Hongo wasn't a slacker.
The mystery expert doesn't know!
but have you seen the movie yet?
I'd love to get this sorted out.
She's totally, completely wrong!
but I kinda liked that about it.
Every bit the cerebral detective.
Now, will there be anything else?
Looks pretty well laid out to me.
Here, I have the meeting minutes.
Yeah, sure, I know what you mean.
And they share a kiss at sunrise.
Isn't it obvious? He's a phantom.
Come on, Chi, let's get you home.
Oh, my god! I can't believe that!
This is the room where Kaito died.
then escaped using the same route.
But we all saw the footage, right?
Thank you. This should be helpful.
What did you think of this theory?
Not very well from the sound of it.
No, maybe the end of May, actually.
Mm-hm. What kind do you read, then?
Old stuff. You know, like Christie.
You really put down a lot of those.
To be honest, I sorta like it, too.
And... You think you have an answer?
My memory's a little bit fuzzy here.
Do you know when she went to see it?
Very passionate. Seriously hardcore.
I suppose you could put it that way.
This is a locked-room murder, right?
I suppose I'd go with something like
This may seem like a silly question,
Didn't that bother you at all, Fuku?
Nakajo's theory is totally out then.
You're saying the scene was adlibbed?
You didn't take into account the fact
Just that any killer with an instinct
We've rejected Nakajo's idea, though.
Obviously, Hongo was a total amateur.
We're interested to hear your theory.
Given the fact his arm was taken off,
Just like with Nakajo's explanation--
Yeah, maybe. But can you disprove it?
I brought these for everyone to share.
Why do think they chose that location?
Let's move on to a different question.
Goin' on about the rules of a mystery.
Except initially, the door was locked.
That doesn't line up with your theory.
I'm not totally convinced, that's all.
Just the standard bestsellers, really.
Actually, I haven't had the chance to.
I don't know, maybe it's silly, but...
Here you are. I've brought the script.
What about the idea to make a movie...
It's like looking into a kaleidoscope.
Would you say it was a difficult shoot?
You're totally right, that's important.
Until she started working on this film,
It seemed like a pretty good one to me.
It's inconsistent with what was filmed.
Sawakiguchi's idea may have been crazy,
There are some inconsistencies, though.
We all saw how detailed the script was.
And what would this particular prop be?
Each of these three has their own theory
I'm curious. When it comes to mysteries,
Or whatever. That might be a bit cheesy.
Thanks for coming all the way to Class F!
Everybody got all fussy about it, though.
It's pretty obvious if ya think about it.
Tomohiro Haba. He's waiting just outside.
Here's another one. They're on here, too!
Heh... It couldn't have been pre-planned,
Well, I suppose I can't really blame you.
It's not the idea itself that's an issue.
You guys are mystery experts or somethin'?
All right then--we'll let you get started.
When are we gonna work on our own mystery?
Plus, it creaked loudly and opened upward.
but without an ending, we're kinda screwed,
How did the crew feel about Hongo's script?
Which she could easily have said to anyone.
He may not wanna come right out and say it,
That is clearly an implausible explanation.
What's this got to do with anything, though?
She didn't make it out to the shoot, either.
It isn't fancy. But it is feasible at least.
But did Hongo see the same problems you did?
I mean, he even made fun of Sherlock Holmes.
Unfortunately, I can't argue with it either.
Hongo had gone there to scope out the place.
There are other windows here, here, and here.
Okay, so what's your mystery genre of choice?
So, what do we think about Haba's conclusion?
I'm not completely convinced that he's right.
But it doesn't work in this particular movie.
If it'll help, you're welcome to take a look.
I'm not sure how many of them get killed off,
Together, they're able to defeat the phantom.
Three possible endings, but none of 'em work.
Do you wanna tell us your theory of the crime?
In other words, it doesn't sit right with you.
All points of escape were effectively blocked,
I think we're getting a little off track here.
And I haven't even told you the best part yet.
If the story was based on the floor plan alone,
Just climb in, do the deed, and climb back out.
It's not like Hongo was an expert on mysteries.
That blows my mind. Didn't see that one coming.
What? I've never heard of a Sherlockian before.
Except... The room where Kaito died was locked.
The one Haba had the foresight to make lots of.
I'm kinda gettin' a weird vibe from these three.
The movie was a blast when we first started out,
But I do think if we can get our hands on a copy
You think you could get us a copy of the script?
The keys were spread out on the table, remember?
I wonder what's gonna happen to their movie now.
Promotional samples of a new product, apparently.
By bus and train, the trip was more than an hour.
but I'm surprised you were allowed to film there.
I think that's just the sort of satisfying ending
The killer couldn't have fled through the window.
All right. I'm ready to hear what you guys think.
A boring old whodunit book? How lame can you get?
the phantom psycho killer appears out of nowhere!
Well, they won't be able to finish it, will they?
I wonder if you might have time for a cup of tea.
"The Case of the Furuoka Deserted Village Murder."
From what we've heard, her writing was consistent.
Would you mind explaining what you meant, exactly?
but Fuku here fancies himself to be a Sherlockian.
Not if you're experienced with this sort of thing.
In order to get to the office where the keys were,
I'm sure you can see where this is leading, right?
Hongo only asked for a small amount of fake blood.
The mystery's solved, and everyone goes home happy.
I betcha Hongo knew that much about mystery flicks.
The killer came in and went out through the window.
Is everybody ready to listen to what I have to say?
Think about what you see if you're renting a movie.
The murderer kills Kaito then climbs out the window.
I dunno... maybe Hongo forgot to write that part in.
Oreki, do you think he's on the right track or what?
Did Hongo volunteer herself to write the screenplay?
So obviously, there must have been a seventh person.
The description in the script seems to back that up.
Sorry we got even more people dragged into this mess.
Hm... No, there's not really anything I can think of.
Given the way he died, you know what this was, right?
Yes, sir, I've got it right here as a matter of fact.
The truth is, I don't really care for mystery novels.
If I were going to decide on a title for the movie...
It's not like I can start making posters or anything.
Not much of a horror movie with only one dead person.
What if she wrote the script without seeing the place?
See? We solved it! The killer fled through the window.
Now we can get back to shooting and finish this movie.
is made problematic itself by the psychology involved.
All in all, this could be a difficult murder to solve.
But honestly, I wasn't too surprised when she got sick.
While I'm looking, you can speak with our props master,
I understand the four of you know your mystery stories.
I can't believe I was so quick to buy that jerk's idea!
And right about the time their paranoia starts to peak,
So then, have you interviewed all the actors about this?
the audience would expect after the horrifying discovery
of the script, that would help us figure some stuff out.
It could be a vengeful spirit! Yeah! That's even better!
there were only two points of access to the murder scene.
I can definitely see flaws in Nakajo's version of events.
I got to thinking while we were listening to Nakajo talk.
What do you think the solution is to this murder mystery?
I'm not saying I like the guy, but there must be a reason
It was just getting out there that was a pain in the butt.
It's the drama of the story that matters, not the details!
It didn't really seem like she had anything fancy in mind.
nothing looked like it was even a little bit out of place.
the building, so we can easily write-off that possibility.
I've heard about the deserted
village in the Narakubo area,
Plus, how could someone reach
that room and still have time
to re-enter from the correct
direction when they regrouped?
Katsuta gave it a good pull
and it still didn't wanna open,
Just think about it: they all
begin to suspect one another.
To see if Hongo said anything
to them that might be helpful?
They wouldn't draw a distinction
between mystery and horror.
I mean, would it have killed
them to choose someplace closer?
So maybe you'd like to hear my
theory about the murderer now?
neatly into place, top to
bottom! And there ya have it. Boom!
You think you could find a
more convoluted way of putting it?
I guess I've read enough of
them to know that much, at least.
Oh, the Nobuhara translation.
Looks like the latest editions.
There are some strange looking
marks here on this paper. See?
She probably just marked the
stories she wanted to draw from.
they would have to risk passing
through the front lobby here.
And the office isn't the only
area the killer couldn't reach.
of Kaito's body. Our props guy
did a great job with that scene.
The door everyone came in
through, and the window on this wall.
We'd like to get a better feel
for Hongo's attention to detail.
Konosu was the one who went
upstairs to the right-hand hallway.
Did Hongo ask for anything
interesting besides the strong rope?
I agree, though, that sounds
more like a bad joke than a movie.
for self-preservation wouldn't
risk going in through the window.
Obviously, the state of the
window wasn't a big concern for her.
It's starting to feel like we're
never going to figure this out.
That works, but it wouldn't make
for a very well-crafted mystery.
If I were the killer, that would
probably be the last way I'd go.
if you think of a mystery as a
contest between author and reader,
We heard that she didn't have a
lot of experience with the genre.
she would have arranged for the
necessary props, don't you think?
The person who recommended it
had an in with the property manager.
Well, at that point in time, the
summer grass hadn't grown in yet!
She used those books to get ideas
for how to write the screenplay.
"Summer grass, 'tis all that
remains of ancient warriors' dreams."
Putting death right there in the
title is a good way to sell seats.
Why don't you give us your
perspective as a member of the film crew?
The other characters enter the
room here, through the right hallway.
since there was no way to guarantee
Kaito would end up in that room.
Could they have used the master
key and then replaced it afterwards?
At least, for someone who doesn't
have experience with these things.
For example, the amount of blood
she asked for wasn't nearly enough.
And that's exactly what Hongo was,
so why shouldn't she start there?
Hongo asked for rope, and he makes
a solid case for his explanation.
That explains why you asked Haba
whether or not he'd seen the movie.
She worked that hard on the script
but then didn't come to the shoot?
Then they return, open the door,
and find Kaito dead inside the room.
an amateur writer like poor Hongo
is bound to come up a little short.
The first point I would make is
that the murder was not premeditated.
It would be impossible to open it
quietly while dangling from a rope.
Hongo was looking for another
actor, in addition to the original six.
But technically speaking, it would
fit with what's been filmed so far.
The performance and production side
of things was pretty fun, actually.
Why's that? Is she the type of
person who gets sick a lot or something?
So two of the characters head back
down the hall to get the master key.
It probably hadn't been opened in
years, since the place was abandoned.
I guess someone recommended it
because it had an interesting look to it.
From the name, I'd say it refers to
a passionate fan of Sherlock Holmes.
in which Kaito was found, but none
of the others could have accessed it.
There's not much I can do on the
publicity front till we've got a title.
If you ask me, your typical viewer
doesn't care about fancy plot devices.
She was teaching herself how to write
a mystery by reading Holmes novels?
I don't think that's what Hongo
intended when she was writing the script.
It's way past time we get this whole
script thing settled, if you ask me.
What seems like a simple solution to
the physical problem of a locked room
Nakajo's idea of a mystery seems as
sophisticated as a kid's picture book.
If you want my opinion, this mystery
is not especially difficult to solve.
I can't say what exactly, but something
about it feels a little off to me.
Look at this note: "Make sure there
are no footprints outside the window."
The problem is that no one could get
into the room where Kaito died, right?
about how the murder mystery is supposed
to play out in the finished script.
Do you think Nakajo's theory is in
line with what Hongo originally intended?
If you go in that way, you're practically
guaranteed to be seen by somebody.
she might have considered other escape
routes for the murderer to have taken.
Hongo went to visit the shoot location
before she started writing the script.
I'm just telling you that everyone
liked Hongo's script. And that includes me!
Walking around in broad daylight,
there's no way you're going to go unnoticed.
I don't think she'd seen any crime
shows or movies or read any mystery novels.
Yeah, she's been absent from school a
whole bunch of times throughout the year.
As assistant director, did you observe
anything else that might be significant?
I think Sherlock Holmes stories are
perfect for newcomers to the mystery genre.
Phantom killers can walk through walls,
can't they? But if that doesn't work...
If Hongo had been planning that kind of
horror twist for the second half of it,
Perhaps Kaito's death could have been a
suicide disguised to look like a murder?
The killer couldn't enter from the first
floor, but what about the second floor?
Actually, if you don't mind me interrupting,
I'd love to know how Hongo is doing.
Remember how I said that Hongo went to
scout out the site back at the end of May?
I am the props master, remember? And
Hongo specifically asked me to procure this.
It's not that I've never read one, it's
just I haven't bothered to in a long time.
For the same reason you already gave.
They couldn't risk walking through the lobby
Fortunately, I had the foresight to
prepare extra so we would have plenty on hand.
There's no way that's how Hongo meant
for it to end when she wrote the screenplay!
Knowing that, we can assume she wasn't
planning on a movie with a high body count.
No matter how much passion goes into a
film, without real skill, it feels amateur.
that we get a look outside the window
after everyone arrives at the scene, did you?
He has his own idea of what a "mystery"
should look like, but what do we all think?
So she probably wouldn't have taken the
grass into account when she wrote the scene.
You never know what information might hold
an important clue. Please, let's continue.
It might not mean anything, but I remember
she made a point to wish Konosu good luck.
That tells us whoever killed Kaito could
not have escaped using conventional methods.
Once his guilt is revealed, the culprit
breaks down in tears and confesses his crimes.
Everybody picked one up at random, and
that's what decided where they went to explore.
The first-floor hallway down the right
side is the only open route leading to the room
No, she didn't have very many requests,
which I think speaks to her lack of experience.
First, I'd like to know what you picture in
your head when you hear the word "mystery."
Konosu is in the Mountaineering Club,
although you wouldn't know it from looking at her.
but I think the best bet is to have one
couple left alive, y'know, for a little romance.
Anyone passing through it would have left a
pretty obvious trail, but from what I recall,
So did Hongo say anything to the actors about
which of them might be playing the murderer?
Except, that doesn't mean much of anything
if Hongo didn't know when she wrote the script.
Think about it from the perspective of someone
who's not all that interested in the genre.
I'd appreciate it if you'd listen to what
they have to say and then tell me what you think.
I couldn't decide if I liked them, so I kept
trying them to see if I could make up my mind.
Even if we say your theory about how it went
down is true, can you tell us who the killer is?
Kaito was found in a room with only one door,
and it was locked. So, how'd the killer get out?
There were two other entry points, but they
were totally blocked with furniture and other junk.
All we have to do is cut the grass and re-shoot
the dead body scene, then everything should fall
That would put them in danger of being seen by
any of the other characters who were moving about
I don't know if that's really how I would describe
it. You might be oversimplifying a little bit.
Rather, circumstances simply fell neatly into
place, and the killer seized that opportunity to act.
And of course, let's not forget the question of
how the killer entered the room in the first place.
If the window was such an important plot point,
she would've checked to see if it would open or not.
aside from the window, and the ground outside of
that showed no sign of having been recently disturbed.
She dangled the rope out the second floor window,
climbed down it to the stage left wing, killed Kaito,
Do we really think Kaito would just stand there
doing nothing while somebody was rattling at the window?
She said we needed to find a rope that was strong
enough that it could support the full weight of a person.
It's all slasher flicks--the kinda stuff that's full
of blood and gore and chainsaws. You know what I mean?