[ERU]
No, I'm serious!
When we played classical music
for our shiitake mushrooms,
their growth rate
increased exponentially!
[MAYAKA]
Really? That's amazing!
Yeah, and if you expose
them to electricity,
like artificial light,
they'll get even bigger.
[MAYAKA]
For real?
[SATOSHI]
Mm-hmm.
When they're stimulated by
a strong current like that,
they feel threatened,
and the fungal filaments respond
by growing bigger to ensure
reproductive success.
[HOTARO] That's fascinating,
but we're here to do homework.
A helicopter?
Mm-hmm.
[HOTARO]
That reminds me...
Wasn't Ogi into helicopters?
[ERU]
Ogi who?
Do you mean Takahiro Ogi
from Class 2-B?
[HOTARO]
No. Who's that?
[ERU] You know. Ogi.
From Class 2-B.
[HOTARO] No, this Ogi taught
at our middle school.
He was an English teacher,
kind of an older guy.
Satoshi. Do you remember him?
I mean, sure,
I remember Mr. Ogi.
but I didn't know he was
really that into helicopters.
I thought everybody
knew about that.
It was the talk of
the school for a bit.
Ibara, does any
of this ring a bell?
No.
[HOTARO]
That's so weird.
How could it have made
such an impression on me,
yet they don't even recall it?
We all went to the same school,
and Ibara and I were
in the same class.
Did I just dream it?
She can't not have known.
[ERU]
Okay.
Is this thing with Mr. Ogi
worth examining further?
No, it's not really a big deal.
Ibara, let me try
to jog your memory.
Now think...
Do you happen to recall
that day when a helicopter
flew over Kaburaya
Middle School?
Um, that happened
like, all the time.
But this time it was strange.
Mr. Ogi stopped teaching
in the middle of class
and ran over to the window to
look at something in the sky.
He stared at this helicopter
until it disappeared,
then said something about
how he loved choppers,
like he was trying to brush
it off as no big deal.
And then he just went
back to teaching, remember?
Oh!
Now that you've
told me the story,
it does sound familiar.
Yeah, I remember that happening.
Are you sure that was Ogi?
Completely sure.
[HOTARO]
That's better.
I felt like I was going crazy.
[SATOSHI]
That is pretty weird.
You're right, it's unusual,
but I swear it happened,
nevertheless.
But when the squadrons
of JSDF helicopters
would fly over,
it was an awesome sight.
We'd all stop and watch.
Even so, I don't
remember Ogi having
a particularly strong
reaction to those.
Hold on a second.
What's a squadron?
A formation.
And how could you
tell they were JSDF?
[SATOSHI] Because I don't know
of any other groups
of helicopters that
fly around in squadrons.
And are you positive Ogi was
around when all that happened?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
Oh!
It was in English class,
'cause I remember looking up
AGM in the English dictionary.
AGM, huh?
And what does that stand for?
[HOTARO] It's an abbreviation
of "air-to-ground missile."
Weird...
I'd think if Ogi
was into choppers
and a squadron flew over,
he'd get up and do a dance.
[SATOSHI] A dance might
be taking it too far.
[HOTARO]
I'm just saying he'd freak out.
Hmm... It's all
coming back to me.
Ogi did go crazy
for helicopters.
I remember hearing that
after starting middle school.
Hmm... It's all
coming back, right?
I even recall wondering if all
the middle school teachers
were as weird as Mr. Ogi.
But like Fuku said
a moment ago,
Ogi never freaked out
about helicopters
after that one flew
over during class.
[HOTARO]
It was three years ago,
but I think I would
remember if Ogi
had done something
similar again.
It was just that one time,
and the way he tried
to cover was weird, too.
There's gotta be
more to this story.
Hey, speaking of Mr. Ogi,
I've suddenly remembered another
incredible story about him.
The man is pretty much a legend.
Don't start making stuff up.
I'm not.
I swear, it actually happened.
I heard this one from
Mr. Ogi himself!
Hmph! This story's insane!
If I hadn't heard it firsthand,
I wouldn't have bought it.
So if you guys don't believe me,
I don't blame ya!
I'm not saying it's
impossible, but still...
Fine, out with it.
Well, according to Mr. Ogi...
...on three separate
occasions...
...he was struck by lightning!
[ERU]
Huh?
You don't mean, like,
lightning lightning, do you?
Mm-hmm.
Lightning!
[HOTARO groans]
Three times?
How could that man be okay?
He was struck three times!
Three times?
How could that man be okay?
[HOTARO] It looks like
Chitanda's learned
to play along with Satoshi.
Although, apparently
the lightning didn't
strike him dead on.
But that still doesn't
mean he walked away
completely unscathed.
He told us he was knocked
unconscious one of those times,
and he has burn marks all
over his entire body, too.
That sounds awful.
But he did live
to tell the tale,
so there is that one
consolation, at the very least.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Even so, why didn't I ever
notice any visible scars?
[HOTARO]
Struck by lightning...
And three times, to boot.
Is something like
that even possible?
We haven't historically
experienced much lightning
here in Kamiyama.
In spite of that,
Ogi claims to have been
struck three times.
Satoshi isn't the type
to lie to his friends
for the sake of a good story.
He even prefaced by saying it
was unbelievable, but true.
If Satoshi was telling the
truth, could Ogi be lying?
It seems like one of those
"stranger than fiction" cases.
[HOTARO]
Wait a minute!
Satoshi.
Don't they keep old
newspapers in the city library?
[SATOSHI] Yes, they do.
Some of them, anyway.
[MAYAKA] We have a few in
the school library, also.
But only ones that pertain
to Kamiyama High.
They won't have
what I need here.
Gotta go.
[HOTARO] I'm heading
to the public library.
You guys wanna come?
[whimpers]
Hotaro, wait.
If I didn't know any better, I
would say you were motivated.
You're wrong!
How should I put it?
I...
I just have to know, okay?
[ALL gasp]
Hotaro?
What have you
done with our friend?!
Are you the energy
conservationist Hotaro Oreki?
Have you been
possessed by an alien?
Or have you been brainwashed
by one Eru Chitanda?
Knock it off!
[MAYAKA] Oreki, you should
go straight home to bed.
Make yourself some tea
and pile on the blankets.
I'm sure you'll be
back to 100% tomorrow.
That's so rude.
Is it that hard to
believe I would take
some spontaneous initiative?
[HOTARO]
Ugh, whatever.
I'll wrap it up in no time.
Hey, Oreki!
Hey, what?
You're just curious, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
You're going to investigate?
Yeah, but who knows if
I'll even turn anything up.
Now I'm curious!
You're what? But why?
Because something has the
power to pique your curiosity!
It's novel for you
to be so intrigued!
I'm dying to know
what quest could have
that kind of
influence over you!
[HOTARO]
This is all incredibly rude.
[HOTARO] Satoshi couldn't
come because he had
too much homework.
He was really
disappointed, though.
Ibara would have
been a lot of help
since she knows the ins
and outs of libraries,
but I couldn't bring
myself to ask.
[ERU]
Thanks for waiting for me!
Okay. Are you ready to go?
Why don't you ride ahead?
I can give you a
lift there, if you want.
[ERU laughs]
[HOTARO]
No way; that's not right.
Nope. Not that, either.
No, you go on.
I'll catch up.
Oh, okay. See ya.
Chitanda!
Yes?
If you happen to come
across the news archives
before I get there,
will you go ahead
and start looking through them
for the name Masakiyo Ogi?
I believe it's written out as,
"small tree that is
correct and pure."
Sure, I'll get right on it.
See you in a few.
[HOTARO]
From what my sister has told me,
having been up into the
Kamikakiuchi mountains
herself several times...
...in such ranges where the
peaks are around 3,000 meters,
the air currents from
below get blocked.
This can cause the
weather to vary greatly
from the near to far sides,
like two completely
different climates.
[HOTARO] I shouldn't keep
Chitanda waiting for too long.
[ERU]
Oreki, you made it!
Look!
I found some information
on Mr. Ogi in the paper!
[HOTARO] "Mountain trail
beautification efforts
in the Kamikakiuchi Range."
It seems like mountaineering
is one of Mr. Ogi's
secret hobbies, huh?
[HOTARO] "The Kamiyama
Mountaineering Association
began sponsoring
beautification efforts
on the Abumidake mountain trail
on the 26th of this month.
Eleven volunteers took part,
primarily picking up litter
and removing overgrowth.
The association's captain,
Masakiyo Ogi, 39,
had this to say:
'The current climbing
boom could bring with it
climbers who might not be
familiar with trail etiquette.
I think it's important
for them to know
that a breach of manners
in this environment
could cost them their lives.'"
I see. That's what I thought.
Oreki, is there
anything the matter?
It's nothing.
Was this the only
mention of him you found
in the newspaper archives?
Yes, but we can ask
at the information desk
on the second floor.
[HOTARO]
It's strange.
I'm kind of hoping
my hunch gets disproven.
[HOTARO]
Excuse me, Miss.
I'd like to do a search of
the newspaper archives.
Sure.
What is it you'd
like to search for?
I'm interested in
local happenings
from April and May
of about three years ago.
[NAKAMURA] Should I search
for specific keywords?
Yes, ma'am.
Try "stranded."
[NAKAMURA]
I've turned up 12 results.
Would you like
to narrow it down?
If that's all there are,
I'd just like to see them.
Sure thing.
[HOTARO]
Eureka.
[ERU] There's an article
from May 9th of that year.
Pardon...
If you wouldn't mind...
We'd like to see
this newspaper article.
[HOTARO] Chitanda can
tell where this is going.
[NAKAMURA] Hey, Maruta,
do you have a minute or two?
[MARUTA]
Hi, may I help you?
Yes, ma'am.
We're interested in reading a
particular newspaper article
from a few years ago.
[MARUTA]
May, three years back.
I'll look for you; hold on.
Sure. Thank you
so much for looking.
It might take about
a half-hour for me
to track down the
article for you, okay?
Sure, we're happy to wait.
[MARUTA] I'll call you
over when it's ready.
We truly appreciate
your help, ma'am.
Hey, Oreki.
Since we'll be here a while,
would you like to look
around for a little bit?
That sounds good.
Oh, is this month's issue
a special on Taira no Kiyomori?
The cover is so beautiful!
[HOTARO] The feature says
that Taira no Kiyomori
was actually the
child of someone
in the Shirakawa palace,
I think.
[ERU]
I've heard that theory.
I'd like to read more
about it, though.
[HOTARO]
Wow, that's pretty impressive.
Miyajima, the island with
the Itsukushima shrine.
I've always wanted to
take a trip to see it.
[ERU]
Look at all of these cabbages!
There are so many
gorgeous colors!
And this page
with all the tomatoes!
They look so juicy
and delicious!
That reminds me, Oreki,
we still have a ton
of shiitake mushrooms
from the harvest!
[HOTARO]
Huh?
[ERU] I can give you some,
if you'd like!
Oh! Look, Oreki, I found
the book on insects!
[ERU]
Dung beetles... interesting.
[giggles]
They're so cute!
[HOTARO]
Not quite how I'd describe them.
Well, Oreki, is there
anything around here
that you'd like to look at?
[HOTARO]
Let me see...
[ERU] Now, that is
what I call a castle.
Your house is huge.
Kind of like a castle, huh?
Do you really think so?
Our house isn't that big.
I would say it's
only a little bit bigger
than a normal house, right?
[HOTARO] I wonder where
she's getting her idea
of a "normal house."
[HOTARO]
So what did you find out?
[MARUTA] It's contained in
this compilation of articles,
so you can find
what you need here.
Thank you very much
for your help.
[HOTARO]
Whoa. It's heavy.
There's a ton of stuff in here.
[ERU] There! That's the
issue from May 9th!
When Ogi stopped
class and voiced his love
for helicopters, it must
have been on this day.
If my theory is correct.
[HOTARO]
Here we go.
Okay, then.
What do you think
all of this means?
Basically...
Mr. Ogi wasn't especially
fond of helicopters.
[HOTARO] But he was struck
by lightning three times.
I think that part
is most likely true.
Although...
He was really just your typical
Kamiyama English teacher.
Not someone likely
to get hit by lightning.
You're right;
that is pretty weird.
But then it hit me,
no pun intended.
What if he frequently
visited a place
where lightning struck a lot
more than it does in town?
Like up in the mountains.
Am I right?
[ERU] So did you have a hunch
that this would be the answer?
[HOTARO]
Something like it, yes.
I figured that even though
he was an English teacher,
mountaineering could've still
been his favorite hobby.
And with that...
I decided to come to the library
and put my theory to the test.
Why did he only look
up at the helicopter
on that day and no others?
Because that particular
helicopter had
a special purpose.
Mr. Ogi was especially
eager to see
that lone helicopter
doing its job.
But... why would he be?
The stakes were high for him.
Mr. Ogi wasn't eager.
He was desperate
to know if the copter
was going to fly that day.
That's why, when
he heard the sound,
he ran over to the window
to see what it was.
Just saying that an
English teacher stops class
to watch a helicopter
doesn't make much sense.
But when you frame it
as a mountaineer
dropping everything
to watch one,
then that's a different story.
Kamiyama sits in the shadow
of the Kamikakiuchi range,
a string of many,
3000-meter-class mountains.
The mountaineers in this town?
They'd pay attention
to helicopters.
Even if they just carried
aerial photographers
over the range.
But this one didn't.
Then what did it carry?
A rescue mission.
[ERU]
Rescue?
The article says
that on May the 8th,
the weather conditions
were severe.
Too bad for a helicopter to fly.
Yeah, I remember.
Ogi was worried the
police wouldn't be able
to send it out on the 9th.
Even while he was teaching,
all he could think about was
the weather up in the mountains.
If it cleared up, the helicopter
would be able to fly,
and the chances of the
stranded mountaineers' survival
would improve.
Imagine what he felt.
He must have been
going through so much.
[HOTARO] I can't speak
to what he was feeling...
...but I do remember
seeing him smile.
[HOTARO] We combed the newspaper
for several days after that.
The bodies of two
climbers were discovered.
They didn't make it, it seems.
They were found by
a police helicopter.
[ERU]
Oreki...
[HOTARO]
Hm?
[ERU] Would it be okay if
I asked you something?
[HOTARO]
Sure. What?
Why were you so
curious about this?
So, what, am I only
allowed to investigate
when you guys are curious?
Oh. You have a point there.
It just doesn't really seem like
something you would do.
Well, I guess you're
right about that.
I mean, after all, my motto is,
"If I don't have to,
I'm not going to."
Yeah, but that's not exactly
what I was trying to say.
[HOTARO] She didn't even bat
an eye at my immutable motto.
[ERU] Oreki, you do work hard
all the time for other people.
You've stepped in to help me
a lot since I've known you.
[HOTARO]
She's got it completely wrong!
[ERU]
However, I've got to say,
you're usually complacent
when it comes
to working for yourself.
But not today.
So I want to know what
made you investigate
for your own sake this time.
I'm sorry.
It's strange, but I just
have to know the answer.
[HOTARO] When Satoshi
told us about the lightning,
my mind associated it
with something awful.
[ERU] Yeah, I remember
you saying that.
[HOTARO]
I wanted to find out whether
I was right about it or not.
That's what motivated
me to investigate.
So then I went to the library.
If all of the research required
had been a major undertaking,
it would've been
a different story.
But since it was just a
matter of flipping through
old newspapers,
it was no big deal.
And you were there to help me.
If it turned out to be true,
then I should be more
careful about things.
What do you mean,
"careful"? How so?
[HOTARO] Maybe "mindful"
is a better word.
With all that happened,
I shouldn't talk about it
as casually as I did.
People died, you know?
The way I spoke
seems insensitive now.
And that's what I have
to be mindful about.
[HOTARO]
Was that hard to follow?
Insensitive's a strong word.
I just mean...
That sense of not taking how the
other guy feels into account.
I'll probably never
see Ogi again--
So his feelings might
not be of much concern.
[ERU]
Oreki...
That's very... I don't know.
I can't think
of the right word.
[HOTARO]
What is she trying to tell me?
Oh, well.
If she can't find
the words for it,
then I'm certainly not
going to press her.
[HOTARO]
Well, I gotta be going.
I really appreciate you
helping me out today, though.
You're very welcome.
Actually, I'm grateful
to have the opportunity
to see this other side of you.
Come on, don't say
stuff like that!
Oh! Sorry, you're right.
[ERU]
I'll see you later.
[HOTARO] By the time
Chitanda gets home,
night will have fallen.
But she's the one
who offered to tag along
in the first place.
I didn't exactly
ask her to help me.
Then again...
...this was my quest.
I owe her one.
[HOTARO] Next time:
"Does Anyone Have Any Idea?"