Please enjoy!
Is something wrong?
Uh... No.
When you asked me if I wanted to have tea
with you, I didn't know you were being literal.
Don't worry. I'll get the tab.
Oh.
Nakajo's theory didn't pan out, then?
Nor Haba's?
Right.
Neither did Sawakiguchi's?
No, I don't believe hers did.
I see.
I'm sorry to disappoint.
You don't have to be nice about it.
I'm incredibly curious.
What was so wrong about their theories?
Well, first, let's talk about Nakajo's hypothesis.
You see? That's why Sawakiguchi's
theory doesn't hold up to scrutiny, either.
Indeed.
Which member of your group
turned down Nakajo's idea, then?
That'd be me.
As well as Haba and Sawakiguchi's ideas?
Yeah, that's right.
When I first approached you about this, you told me
I shouldn't expect too much from you.
I guess our standards of expectation differ.
Because you proceeded to disprove
the theories our detectives put forth.
But to be honest, that was my expectation.
You knew I'd disprove them?
I never thought they'd be up to the challenge.
I was right.
None of them possesses the level of deductive
reasoning skills necessary to tackle something like this.
You mean the whole detective thing was a ruse?
Of course.
I'm not calling them incompetent.
They have their own strengths, to be sure.
But that doesn't make them useful to me in a
situation like this, and I had to interest you somehow.
Why not just...
If it weren't for you.
If it weren't for you, we would have gone
with one of their ideas, and the whole production
would have ended in failure.
And I refuse to have my name attached
to anything that isn't a success.
Man, that's pretty cold. You're heartless, aren't you?
If I must be cruel in order to get the best
product, so be it. I will do whatever it takes.
I had heard from three different
people that only you could fix this.
Eru Chitanda said it,
as well as someone from outside our school.
Masashi Togaito championed your prowess, too.
When I learned of your reputation, I was convinced
you had to be our detective and save our film.
There was no doubt in my mind.
I was after you from the very beginning.
Not the Classic Lit Club.
So, Oreki.
After carefully weighing all the rumors about you
against your own assessment of the detectives' theories,
I have decided.
It's all true.
You are special.
You're gifted. A true genius.
So I'll ask again: will you help us?
Say yes.
You are the only person who can save our class project.
I couldn't bear it if all that hard work went to waste.
I'm really not a genius.
I just... get lucky from time to time.
That's a real shame.
Let me tell you a little story.
It might change your perspective a bit.
Once, there was a sports team with a benchwarmer.
The benchwarmer did her very best to get
herself off the bench and onto the field,
but all her efforts were in vain.
Try as she might, her hard work was no match
for the athletic ability of the other team members.
There was one player in particular
whose natural talent was undeniable.
Compared to our benchwarmer, the
difference was like night and day.
At one match, the talented girl performed
exceptionally well, even for her, and was named the MVP.
Interviewers flocked to her, hungry for a quote.
One said, "You're amazing!
We're dying to know your secrets!"
She answered humbly.
"Secrets? Oh, no, I just got lucky!"
I believe the poor benchwarmer took great
offense upon hearing such an inconsiderate remark.
Do you?
It's not wrong to acknowledge who you really are.
If you don't,
you make fools out of those who praise you.
Is she right? Am I special?
Do I deny myself credit for being who I am?
If so, then why?
Do I think it's wrong to believe in my talent?
All right, Irisu.
My answer...
You're going to school of your own accord
during summer vacation? Are pigs flying?
Do you have to?
No, but am I not allowed to go to school if I want to?
You are.
It's just not like you, that's all.
I'm fulfilling a personal request from Irisu.
I'm going to solve the murder in Class 2-F's film.
What? No way! Who are you?
I am Hotaro Oreki, the hard-working teenage detective.
Did you say "hard-working"?
This is spooky.
Hmph.
Seriously, I never thought I would see the day.
Are you doing this because of Chitanda again?
No.
Then, what's your motivation?
"If I don't have to, I'm not going to," remember?
That is your motto. Am I correct?
Satoshi.
Hm?
Ah...
Please be honest.
Do you believe that there's
anything which only you can do?
No way.
Really?
Don't you remember?
I don't have any special talents.
Here, check it out.
I think of myself as a Sherlockian.
But I know deep down that I couldn't really be one.
I don't have the kind of iron-clad
constitution that could handle diving headlong
into the murky depths of obscure knowledge.
I'm nothing but an impostor.
If Mayaka suddenly took a
serious interest in Sherlock Holmes,
I guarantee this: She'd surpass me in three months, flat.
I'm a jack of all trades, but a master of none.
I'm a serious dabbler, that's all.
I get my passport stamped and I go on my way.
I'm an expert at nothing, but that's all right.
But, I get it.
Irisu roped you into this somehow.
Even so, you still doubt your aptitude.
Which is normal, I suppose.
Don't you have any doubts about yourself?
Even a little?
I don't. I know I'm average.
Let's go.
Mayaka is probably at school already.
I wanna say hi.
Satoshi!
Hm?
What I think may not matter, one way or the other,
but, in my opinion, you're way better than just average.
If you wanted to be a Sherlockian someday,
I believe that you would be one
of the finest Japan had to offer.
There are about a million things I'd
rather aspire to than being a Sherlockian.
Though I've gotta admit...
I couldn't envy you more.
Just so you know.
What?! It's summer vacation and Oreki
still came to school of his own accord?
You got a problem with that?
It's creepy.
I'm sure it foretells some kind of apocalyptic disaster.
Look, I decided to help solve the mystery.
Seriously? How come?
He, he.
I bet Irisu seduced you into it somehow, didn't she?
You nailed it. Sharp as a tack!
Whatever.
Enough about me, what happened after you left yesterday?
You mean with Chi?
Well, I know she made it home all right.
But when I called her this morning,
she was in bed with a hangover.
That's funny.
And all from those chocolates.
Ahem.
Well, anyway.
I think it would help if we watched the movie again.
Kaito!
Th-There's blood everywhere!
Oh, no. What is that?
Wow, Kaito's severed arm looks so lifelike
in that shot. I'd swear that it was real!
I think the prop team is the most
talented part of this entire production.
Oh, no.
It sure doesn't seem like a very
complicated set-up from my perspective.
That's true. They did an excellent
job of making it look simple, huh?
No, they didn't.
The reason the setting looks so simple doesn't
have anything to do with the filmmakers at all.
What, then?
Here's my assessment:
Anything good in this film is a complete accident.
They don't know what they are doing,
so the mystery ends up falling flat.
Damn.
These students from Class 2-F have
decided to participate in the Kanyasai.
You're right.
The first time I saw it, I assumed at this point
it was a regular documentary, not a murder mystery.
The production values are extremely weak, overall.
Like, which part?
The camerawork, for starters.
Yeah, I agree.
Okay.
How would you shoot it, Ibara?
Well, I'm glad you asked.
Let's see. Where was it?
Hold on. Right here.
Wouldn't it be better to use a wide shot here?
Just to give some perspective on the size of
the room and how small the characters are in it?
Good point.
And, also...
This part.
Hey, Sugimura!
What did you find up there?
Well, it's pretty clean, mostly.
The rooms in this wing...
I think it would be smarter to shoot
from Sugimura's perspective, so the audience
could see that the lobby's in full view from up there.
If the viewers only see him from down there,
there's no way they would be able to tell that.
Okay.
What else is there?
You know...
How 'bout we not?
What, how come?
You'll never stop.
Plus, criticizing the camerawork won't solve the mystery.
Now, now.
There might be some value in criticism.
There you are! Finally!
Uh... Ah, ha...
So this is where you've been hiding!
Yamauchi! How's it going?
Whoa!
Hey, man, no need to resort to violence!
It's for your own good!
You should be thanking me!
Come on!
I've got a ton of other things to do today!
Dummy! Omichi's gonna shred you!
Don't you even care if you fail the class?
Go with him.
You do need those remedial lessons.
No! Solving Hongo's mystery is just as important as math!
Come on, Hotaro, just pull the answer out of thin air!
What are you even talkin' about, you moron?
Oh, it's fascinating...
No! Let me stay!
I have to know the answer! The answer!
He put up a good fight.
What is wrong with that boy?
He's not giving up!
I'm sorry, my friends.
I'm a slave to circumstances beyond my control.
Though it's come to this.
Fukube!
Think of this notebook as me and I shall be with you.
Stand up! Let's go!
Okay! I'm coming. Don't drag me!
Ridiculous.
Well then,
I guess I'd better go, too.
Really?
Don't give me that look.
Helping Irisu is one thing, but I'm
making no sacrifices for the likes of you.
Oh, yeah?
Such attitude.
I have library duty today.
If you'd told me before, I could have cancelled it.
It's your own fault for springing this on us.
That said...
I'm sorry. I mean it.
Okay.
Let's split up and explore the building!
Hey!
Damn it! He's dead!
Th-There's blood everywhere!
There has to be a set of keys
lying around this place somewhere.
I've got it.
So, that's it.
That's what she intended.
Come in.
First, I have to know.
Did you figure it out?
Okay. Then let me hear it.
Right.
It goes without saying that the locked room is key here.
No pun intended.
At the time he died... I mean...
at the point in which he was murdered in the movie,
none of the others could have entered
or left that room without being noticed.
There's nothing to be nervous about here.
Uh...
The stage left wing was also locked.
Damn it! He's dead!
The window, which is the only
other way out, is difficult to open.
That means it's not possible for the killer
to have come or gone by any way except the door.
So how'd they get in the room?
I can't tell from the video if there's some rig
built into the door that springs the lock.
So it's safe to assume that the killer
used the master key to let themselves in.
However, Sugimura was able to see the lobby.
Because of Sugimura, no one could have entered the
stage right hallway, which creates a second locked room.
They couldn't have gotten the master key
from out of the office and gone down that hall
without going through the lobby.
He'd spot them.
So what possible explanations does that leave?
If none of the six could have done it
without being seen, there's just one answer.
A seventh character must have committed the murder.
Interesting. Sawakiguchi said that.
Yes.
When she first brought it up to us, I thought
it was ridiculous, and I wrote it off completely.
It didn't seem like a viable option.
But then she said that Hongo was
trying to cast a seventh character.
Remembering that piece is what ultimately convinced me.
But...
Hongo had written the rest of the
film's script to be pretty straightforward.
It seemed unlikely that she'd
introduce a new character at that point.
However,
we noticed a few odd occurrences
at other points in the film.
Satoshi pointed them out for me in his notes.
"Konosu finds the floorplan. It seems illuminated.
I think it's lit by a flashlight."
"I saw it again.
In the part where they go looking for Kaito."
"The hall is pitch black. Can't see a thing.
Suddenly, a flashlight, again."
What's weird about a flashlight?
Nothing.
Except that none of the six kids is ever seen
holding one at any other point in the whole movie.
If you look closely at the scene
where they discover Kaito's body,
immediately after the illumination in the hallway,
you can clearly see that no one has a flashlight.
There was enough time for them to have hidden it,
but why would they do that?
There's no good reason to.
I know, I know.
You assumed it's scene lighting, but hold that thought.
Just keep everything I said about
the flashlight in mind for later.
There's something else.
And don't get offended. Know
it's coming from a true film buff.
She complains that the movie is boring.
And it's poorly produced.
The camerawork in particular
lacked any innovation or skill.
But what if that was intentional?
A clue for the viewers?
How was it shot?
The camera appears to be in the same
place as the other six for the whole movie.
Well, then,
it seems like you've figured it out.
I think I have.
Do you mean...
...that the cameraman is the
seventh character and the killer?
Mm-hm.
There were seven characters
from the beginning of the film.
The six that you see on screen the entire
time, and the person behind the camera shooting.
That makes seven.
Now, watch closely.
In some of the scenes, the actors
seem to be aware of the camera.
They pay subtle attention to him.
They look at him occasionally, though not very much.
Calling him the cameraman is confusing.
Let's rename him the seventh man.
Now remember the flashlight.
It wouldn't be odd for him to be carrying
one, if it's his job to chronicle the experience.
The poor quality of the camera work, and
the fact that none of the scenes were shot
from multiple angles makes sense.
If the guy behind the camera is a
character in the story, that's expected.
Also...
and this part is really important...
When the characters split up to look
around, the camera stayed in the lobby
after all six of the others had left.
There's that weird, empty moment, and the scene fades out.
So check it out.
After the others were gone, the seventh
man stopped filming for a few minutes, left.
Came back, started rolling, and waited for them.
And so, it was a really simple crime.
The seventh man made sure they were gone, stopped
his camera, and ran to the office to get the master key.
Then, while the others were busy
elsewhere, he found Kaito and killed him.
After he committed the murder, he used
the master key to lock the room behind him.
Then he returned quickly to the
lobby and waited for the others.
That is the conclusion I drew.
If Hongo hadn't already cast a seventh actor,
then I suggest you try to find one as soon as possible.
Two questions.
First, if your theory is true, the fact that no one
ever talks to the seventh man or acknowledges him much
seems a little awkward, doesn't it?
Maybe Hongo was using that as a way to establish a motive.
The seventh man could be an outcast,
someone that others usually ignore.
As a result, he never felt confident speaking
up when they were around, hence his silence.
Next question.
If your hypothesis is correct, wouldn't the other
characters figure it out eventually, the same as you did?
They would all suspect the seventh
man because he'd stayed in the lobby.
Also, the "second locked room"
part of your theory is still intact.
His exit from the lobby and his return after the
murder would have been in public view the whole time.
In which case, everyone would know
who the murderer was immediately.
I don't mean to be rude when I say this, but,
what does it matter? Like, who cares?
It's not important whether the
characters know who the killer is or not.
As long as the audience is intrigued by the
mystery, don't you think that's the point here?
That may be the reason the film doesn't
have a detective character in the first place.
The movie doesn't deal with the
people in the story figuring it out.
They know who among them would be the killer.
Congratulations.
Huh?
I believe that you have just solved Hongo's mystery.
It's an astoundingly bold approach.
That's for certain, but it
corresponds to all of the facts,
so I can't imagine there's any
legitimate reason to dispute it.
Anyway, thank you.
Now we can resume our production.
I guess my assumption about
you has proven correct after all.
You do have formidable skill.
The power no one else possesses.
Uh, thank you.
That's nice to hear. I'm very flattered.
I mean it.
So, what do you think the title of our film should be?
Oh, the title?
Off the top of your head. I'm sure everyone will
approve, and I know I would like anything you dream up.
Huh.
Well, let me think.
In light of the culprit...
How do you feel about, A Blind Spot to All?
That's a good idea.
I think it's the one.
Home run.
Good morning!
All the third years, please listen up.
It's October, time for everyone's favorite:
the cultural festival!
It's strange. How could anyone have
gotten into that room without us seeing?
I don't know. But I think...
...there's one person who could've. Did you murder Kaito?
You did it, didn't you?
Murderer!
You're gonna pay for this!
Turned out great, huh?
You can't run away from this!
He pulled it off, didn't he?
Man, I gotta tell ya,
I was amazed by that surprise ending!
It's the real-life Kaito!
Hey, you're the guy!
Everybody's saying you're the
mastermind behind the whole thing.
Yeah. Sure.
Man, that ending was genius, kid!
Sure surprised me!
Hey! It's The Great Detective!
"Great detective"?
Yeah! Good work!
Though, I have to say, it's sad that
when the seventh character is revealed
to be the killer, the others turn violent, too.
They should have just turned him in.
Yeah.
Well, anyway, thanks for everything.
See ya!
Cool.
Listen, Nakajo...
What's up?
Your pit stains are out of control.
That arm was worth all the work we put into it.
Tch.
I guess Haba wasn't satisfied with the ending.
Hotaro!
Huh?
We saw the film.
What did you think?
It's pretty good.
It was very interesting.
Who would've have pinned it on the cameraman?
The other day when we met.
Had you already figured it all out?
No, at that point, I hadn't quite come up with it yet.
Really.
Huh?
Weird.
She doesn't seem surprised at all.
Then again, it is Mayaka. What'd I expect?
Hey, Oreki.
Hm? Yeah?
Listen.
I-I thought...
I'll tell you later.
Well, you did a great job, as usual, my friend.
And as for the Empress. She's happy.
Plus the audience loved the element of
surprise with the seventh man at the end.
Oreki...
There's something I have to ask.
What's that?
What are you doing?
Now you're solely responsible for that ending, aren't you?
That's right.
All of it?
Mostly.
Hm...
Then how do you account for what Haba
said when we met with the detectives?
Haba?
It's just...
They didn't use a rope anywhere in that
movie, and Hongo specifically asked him for one.
Next time:
"Credit Roll of Fools."