I appreciate the lunch and all, Sis,
but I have no idea what half this stuff is.
Here goes nothing.
We're back!
Thank you for holding down the fort.
Sure.
Anyway... we were victorious!
It did come down to the wire.
Congrats. I'm happy for you.
In a way, it's your victory too.
There's no chance we could have won without your help.
No big deal. Really.
You know, I didn't see that coming.
It was very out of character.
Staging a dramatic rescue? I wasn't expecting that one,
I guess I was caught up in the festival mood.
It won't happen again.
Can you do me a favor?
There's something I would
really like you to take a look at.
Here it is.
So, somebody stole a ladle from the Cooking Club?
Yeah... Just the one from our table, though.
Sounds like someone has too much time on their hands.
It's not just the Cooking Club.
The same kinda thing's happened to
the Go Club and the Acapella Club.
And the Fortunetelling Club.
A note was left there, too!
Let's see... what did it say again?
Yeah, somebody's got way too much time on their hands.
Think I can finish my lunch now?
Oreki!
Oh, no. Here we go again.
There's no escaping the
unbearable curiosity of Eru Chitanda.
Who would do something like this in
the middle of the cultural festival?
Why are they appropriating Jumonji's name?
Why are they stealing all these random items?
I just... I have to know!
We don't have time for a new mystery.
We need to sell these...
Speaking of the anthologies...
...we need a new plan.
We've been publicizing them during our other
events, but it doesn't seem to be doing much good.
That's true.
We need to come up with something that's
going to grab more people's attention.
Right! That's my point.
What if we pitch this phantom
thievery to the Wall Newspaper Club?
And maybe we can have the school
radio do a report about it too.
With that publicity, people will
be dying to read the anthology.
Makes sense to me.
That could be exactly what we need!
But what kind of pitch are you going to give them?
This has nothing to do with the Classic Lit Club.
I'm glad you asked.
The Classic Lit Club's master detective, Hotaro
Oreki, will set out to catch the phantom thief
who is plaguing the festival!
To learn more about his past exploits, check
out the Classic Lit Club's anthology, Hyouka!
Who wouldn't want one after that?
Yeah, it was okay, I guess.
Right? We'll unmask Jumonji and
publicize the anthology at the same time!
Count me out!
What do you think I am, huh?
Some monkey that you can use to lure in customers? Hmph!
Can't we just give it a try? Pretty please?
Oh, come on.
Even if I did play along with this,
there are a thousand students here.
Add in all the visitors, and
the number goes up even higher.
How are we supposed to catch
one thief out of so many people?
Is it that hard? Really?
Impossible.
Maybe if we got involved some other way.
Like if the thief targeted the
Classic Lit Club or something.
Yeah. Well...
We could stage a robbery!
No way!
Kidding!
Really! I swear! I was just kidding.
Speaking of targets...
Which clubs have had things stolen so far?
Go, acapella, cooking, and I uh... I forget.
The Fortunetelling Club.
Yeah. Right!
The Acapella Club,
the Go Club, The Fortunetelling Club,
and the Cooking Club?
ABC!
Huh? Huh?
Hello, Suzuki?
It looks like the clubs that could go with "E" are
the Film Club, the Gardening Club, and the SF club.
I'm lost. What's going on?
The thefts follow a pattern.
And it's not an especially complex one, either.
The Acapella Club, the Igo Club,
the Uranai Club.
Skip a letter to the Oryori Club,
and if an "E" club pops up next...
Japanese alphabetic order!
That would be my guess.
The Gardening Club has been hit.
They stepped out for a second and
one of their water guns was stolen.
A water gun?
Fire safety for roasting potatoes.
One of their members came in here with one yesterday.
Just a second.
In Christie's The ABC Murders, a
person whose name starts with an "A"
is killed in a town whose name starts with "A."
An otama was stolen from the Oryori Club.
Wait, hold on.
Right.
What did the Fortunetelling Club lose? Do you know?
Oh... yes!
The Wheel of Fortune. A Tarot card.
Okay. Take a look.
The Gardening Club's water pistol was an AK,
wasn't it?
An AK? What's that?
A Russian-made assault rifle.
So it's an AK for the Engei
Club, and ishi for the Igo Club?
That works. What about the Acapella Club?
I think we're missing the most important thing.
And what's that?
Our phantom thief's signature.
Yeah, it says Jumonji.
Does it, though?
Wouldn't the usual reading be "jumoji"?
"Tenth letter"!
A-I-U-E-O, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko,
up to the tenth letter!
"Ko!" The Koten Club!
Otherwise known as the Classic Lit Club.
I don't know about you, but I'd say
that's probably enough for a pitch.
I need to get to the Wall Newspaper
Club and tell them about this!
She's pretty excited, huh?
What's wrong?
Huh?
Oh... I just thought of something, that's all.
This whole thing...
You know, never mind. I gotta go.
That's weird. What's with him?
Who knows?
Shouldn't you be getting back to the Manga Club?
Soon enough.
Hmm...
Why? You trying to get rid of me?
Well, are you?
Cranky today.
No, I am not!
The trick to negotiating.
First, make it seem like you
expect something of the other person.
Second, downplay the benefit
that you will receive from it,
and third, ask someone of the
opposite sex, away from public view.
All right!
On it!
I'll go interview the Gardening Club!
Hey! What about Acapella?
I'm calling them right now!
Hurry it up, will you?
I'm sorry. Excuse me!
Sorry about this, Chitanda,
but we're a little busy right now.
Think you could drop by another time?
Oh, okay. I'll come back later.
Actually, no!
I need to talk to you right now!
If it's about your club, I told
you... We need a special angle...
That's just it. We do have an angle!
Yeah? What's that?
I know that! Stop rushing me!
Never mind, let's change gears.
What are we doing about that interview?
Do you think we could hurry this up?
I'm really...
Whoa! Hey!
Where are we going?
The thing is, there's some stuff going on, and I
really felt like I needed to tell someone about it.
So... uh...
I came here. I trust you.
Oh... Yeah?
Thanks, I guess...?
But honestly, there's not much
in it for the Classic Lit Club.
'Kay...
What do you think? Can you help, Togaito?
Is this something you can do for me?
Uh... well...
Honestly, I'm a little confused.
Oh, sorry.
Anyway, like I said, we're busy right now.
Come back later after you've gathered your thoughts.
No...
Please wait!
Somebody at the festival is stealing things
from various clubs for no apparent reason!
There! That's the story!
Jumonji!
That's who you mean!
Do you know something?
Huh? Well... uh...
Right, alphabetical order. I see the pattern.
And you say the Fortunetelling Club got hit, too.
So that's why, then.
So that's why what?
Oh. We're the Kabe Newspaper Club.
They got you too?
Jumonji took our kata knife.
I guess that explains why all of
you are running around like crazy.
Yeah.
I don't usually like being stolen from,
but at least we got a good story out of it.
I'm impressed. Your club figured out a lot.
It was mainly Oreki. You remember him.
Yeah. Sure.
Anyway, thanks for the tip. Appreciate it!
Please wait, Togaito!
I gave you some helpful information.
I hope you'll write about the Classic Lit Club now!
You will... right?
I kind of lost my cool toward the end there.
I hope Togatio doesn't think I was doubting his integrity.
Excuse me!
Sorry!
Oh, it's you. Well? Did you have any luck?
Oh... well...
That's a good question.
Sorry, never mind. It's an inside joke.
Okay.
Well, anyway, I finally heard back from the Acapella Club.
Looks like it was apple juice that was taken.
Turns out the Wall Newspaper Club was targeted, too.
Apparently they had their cutter knife stolen.
Right. "Ka."
Japanese alphabetical order for sure.
Next up is the letter "ki," which
can only be the Kijutsu, or Magic Club.
Fortunately, it's almost time for the next performance,
and I think I'm gonna go.
You wanna catch Jumoji in the act?
Yep.
That's a big weakness for this kind of thief.
He's bound by his own rules, so he's predictable.
We just have to anticipate Jumoji's
next move, and the thief will be unmasked.
But if we catch him at "ki," then it will all be over.
And the culprit will never have
made it to the Classic Lit Club.
That's all right.
I'm sure we can figure something out.
Really? Like what, exactly?
Let's talk later, but now I need to get to the Magic Club.
Gotta catch a thief. See ya!
It's still only 2:00.
Ah, well, look who it is.
Hey. How's it going?
If you're standing around waiting for
the show to start, that means you must know.
Know what?
Don't play dumb with me!
You know about the phantom thief Jumoji.
Oh. That...
Good, then this will be our next competition.
You know about the Newspaper Club?
The cutter knife, you mean?
Sure, I heard about it.
Yeah. Obviously, they've taken
an interest in the crime spree.
Jumoji is the next issue's top story.
What's more, they're going to run an extra,
exclusively covering any group
that catches the phantom thief.
Yeah.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but I've got this one in the bag.
Because you know who's a major mystery fan?
That's right! It's me!
Go easy on me, okay?
Ibara.
You're a Christie fan, right?
So you must have read The ABC Murders at some point.
Yeah, of course I have.
Then can you tell me something?
Was there a reason why the killings
were done in alphabetical order?
Spoiler alert! Are you sure?
Go ahead.
"He wanted to kill in alphabetical order,
so that's what he did."
Not exactly much of a motivation, is it?
No.
Do you think the same thing is going on here?
I don't know.
Anybody would have figured out the
pattern the thefts were following eventually.
Surely Jumoji would have realized that.
So why do it that way, then?
Right, that's what I'm wondering.
Is there some kind of hidden purpose or meaning
behind the way in which things are being stolen?
Still, it is possible Jumoji's doing it just for fun.
Hmm... Interesting.
You really want to catch the thief now, don't you?
You think so? Why's that?
You're pretty intent.
I don't care one way or another.
But once Chitanda says she's curious about
something, it becomes an issue that can't be avoided.
Why don't you just ignore her?
She's not someone I can easily
ignore, or trust me, I would.
Right, I get it.
Okay, then.
You're leaving?
Yep.
Oh, and by the way, thank you for the flour.
It was a big help.
Oh! I almost forgot.
Really? You're charging me?
No, it's not like that.
It's the Warashibe Protocol.
I need you to give me something in return for the flour.
You do?
Like in the old folk tale.
The guy starts with a piece of
straw and trades till he gets rich.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Let's see...
You can have this.
Are you sure?
Yep.
Really? Can you cosplay without I... Ah!
Don't call it that, you idiot!
The show will be starting soon.
Please take your seats, everybody.
Irisu! Over here.
Oh. Hello.
I can't wait for the show. You?
I'm not sure how much I like magic, but here I am.
Yeah. It's something to do, right?
Could she be...?
That's crazy.
I mean, come on.
He didn't have to say it like that...
That's the Manga Club president.
I saw her at their booth yesterday.
Well, this should be fun.
Oh... Hey, look!
Tanabe just walked in.
And look at that!
He's with the Student Council
President, Muneyoshi Kugayama.
Hey, Empress.
Hello.
Hi.
Hey, Fukube.
Hi!
Thank you for your patience! The
Magic Club's performance will now begin.
We're glad to see so many friendly
faces in the audience this afternoon.
We hope you'll enjoy the show
that we've put together for you
and the tricks we've worked long and hard to master!
Now, then...
With this many people watching the show,
how will you commit your crime, phantom thief Jumoji?
Yoichi Takamura will perform "Living Dead."
What's wrong?
Well...
Candle!
Sorry. Don't mind me.
Damn!
When...?
I was watching, and nobody but
the performers went near the stage.
Which means... it was taken before they started.
Ugh. Coming here was a waste of time!
What made me so sure he would steal
something during the performance, anyway?
I'm an idiot!
Thanks a lot! Have a good day!
We're selling more than yesterday, right?
Yeah, we are.
I guess the posters are helping.
That's great!
Obviously, we should have just done
what Kochi said from the very beginning.
Yeah.
If a certain someone hadn't thrown a fit, I
bet we could have sold a bunch more yesterday.
Careful, now.
We don't want to hurt anyone's feelings, do we?
Try to ignore them.
Yeah.
And after all that, she couldn't find the thing?
A total lie, right?
I'm sure she just got scared that the manga she
was going on about was actually nothing special.
How pathetic! Bringing up some amateur
title just to make yourself look smart.
Yeah, totally!
How much you want to bet that manga doesn't even exist?
...Hey, hold on...
...Stop! That's enough.
If you've never heard of it, you can keep quiet.
Hi, everyone.
I-I was just saying...
Well now I'm saying.
If you don't know anything, you
should just keep your mouth shut.
So anyway...
How was the Magic Club show?
Good. I really enjoyed it.
Yeah?
Maybe I could go and check it out tomorrow, then.
Okay. That should be fine.
What time does it start?
They do performances throughout the day,
so I'm sure you can make it to one of them.
Really? Thanks a lo...
Sorry. Think I can take a break?
Sure. No problem.
Hey!
I really am pathetic.
I just want someone to tell me it'll be okay.
Ibara?
Uh... Yes!
What's up, Yuasa?
I'm really sorry.
Things have gotten pretty awkward, huh?
I don't know why you're apologizing.
For not saying anything sooner.
I should have taken your side before, and I didn't.
Except, if you had stood up for me yesterday, there
probably would've been friction between you and Kochi,
and I wouldn't want that to happen.
I think it's better this way.
It's all bluster.
Ayako doesn't mean it.
Ayako?
Ayako Kochi. That's her full name.
Oh.
She seemed pretty serious, so what
makes you think she didn't mean it?
Because I know her. She and I are friends.
Is that it?
There's also the fact that she and Haruna were friends.
Sorry. Who's Haruna?
Haruna Anjo. Don't you know? She's one
of the authors of A Corpse by Evening.
It was a collaborative work?
Somebody else did the art for it.
Ayako would probably know who it was.
Can I talk to Haruna? What class is she in?
Well, she doesn't go here
anymore. She transferred schools.
Really? Too bad.
But even if they were good friends, what does that matter?
Friends don't agree on everything.
Maybe this was something they disagreed about.
Yes, that's a good point, but sorry.
I really shouldn't say any
more than I've already told you.
I mean... Ayako is my friend, after all.
And explaining why you think what
you do would mean speaking badly of her?
I think I need a little more time alone.
Are you sure?
It's okay. I won't be much longer.
Extra! Extra!
It's a must-read, kids!
He did come through!
Bad news. I've been had!
There was a candle stolen from the Magic Club earlier.
They even found the standard confession note.
Isn't that good news, though?
We don't want the thief caught before
he hits the Classic Lit Club, right?
Yeah. I know that's what we decided.
But I thought maybe I could catch him red-handed.
You hoped the theft would happen during the performance?
Yeah.
Jumoji doesn't really seem to
want an audience for the thefts.
I mean, the Cooking Club's ladle
disappeared before the contest, right?
If you realized that, then why not say something?
It's not like you told me you were going
to the Magic Club to catch him in the act.
Yeah. I guess that's true.
Hey, guys, I'm back!
And I'm happy to report that the 20 volumes of
Hyouka we left with Irisu are selling at a good pace!
Irisu could sell a glass of water to a drowning man.
There's one other thing, too.
In their 4:00 edition, the Wall Newspaper Club
has included an article that covers the Jumoji case.
It also mentions the alphabetical
order pattern of the crimes.
Cool.
The best part is that we're in the story, too.
It says that the final item will be taken from
either the Industrial Arts Club or the Classic Lit Club.
An IA club? We have one of those?
Yeah, we do. Guess I forgot.
If they get hit, then our
whole plan goes up in smoke, huh?
I'm thinking about making a deal
with the Broadcasting Club tomorrow.
If we can get them to give us some
airtime, that would be great publicity.
What? Is something wrong?
Well... It's just...
You look... tired.
Man, am I tired.
Oh. Mayaka.
So how were our sales today?
Not counting the ones we gave
Irisu, we managed to sell 16.
Not that bad.
I guess so. Yeah.
It could be worse.
As president, it's my job to go around
recruiting people to help us sell the anthology.
But honestly... I'm getting worn out.
Body Talk.
There's no denying it's a step below A Corpse by Evening.
But still, it's pretty good.
Ugh. My stuff is a hundred steps below.
Hotaro's changed.
No, more like he's finally showing his true potential.
And it's all because he met Chitanda.
She's brought an element of unpredictability
into his life that's forcing him to grow.
I should be happy for him.
And I am, really.
It's just sometimes I wish...
There are over a thousand suspects.
There's no way that simple deduction is going
to be able to whittle down a list that long.
Which means that our best shot at solving this mystery
is catching the thief in the act.
I don't know if Hotaro will be able to solve this one,
but I think I can.
Hotaro. I'm going to catch Jumoji, just you watch.
They do mail order too?
Next time:
"The Final Target."