Oh.
No.
Yes?
Yes.
Huh?
Hmm?
Yep!
Huh?
Yes.
Hey.
Yeah.
Oh...
What?
Sure.
Yeah!
Kaho!
'Kay?
True.
Yeah?
Whoa!
Yeah.
Yeah!
Sorry.
Right.
Haori?
Oreki?
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Mayaka!
Really?
Thanks.
Mayaka.
String?
...Here.
Me, too.
Perfect.
So sorry.
Chitanda?
Oh, right.
It's cold.
Huh? Yeah.
...Thanks.
Number 16.
It's fine!
Oh. Right!
Fuku, hey.
Too short.
Next time:
What is it?
Hello, sir.
Yeah, I am.
Hey, Oreki.
Ah... Ah...
Oh my gosh!
This is...!
Hermit crab?
Hey, Mayaka!
Don't stare.
Here you go.
I hear that.
Ah. Jumonji.
What's that?
That's okay.
I'm so sorry.
Sure doesn't.
What the...?!
Hey, Chitanda.
What did I do?
Just fortunes.
This isn't it.
I'll fix that!
Hold on! Wait!
This is awful.
Happy New Year.
May I help you?
Happy New Year!
Go ahead, then.
Anyway, Oreki...
No plans so far.
Where's Satoshi?
Where is Fukube?
I got number 10!
Wow! Great luck!
That's terrible!
That might work!
You've saved us.
Visit the shrine?
Ah! Hello, Oreki!
Can I carry that?
A bottle of saké.
The storehouse...
Yeah, I think so.
I can't say that.
What do you mean?
I don't have one.
You can see that?
Oh, that's right.
Is that a string?
Sorry 'bout this.
Well, yeah. Maybe.
I was wondering...
I think that's it.
The shrine office.
She had it before!
Is that you, Oreki?
Very distinguished.
I accept this gift.
Is it long-sleeved?
If you say so, sir.
I want to help you.
No, the storehouse.
Ah! I'm very sorry.
Back to square one.
Bingo! I was right!
Yeah, check it out.
I'll be right back!
Thanks for offering.
You can go on ahead.
That's awesome, Chi!
No, I'm not excited,
No, never mind that.
Whew, it's freezing.
But this is strange.
I'm sorry, Chitanda.
Let's call for help.
Um, no, not exactly.
And I was thinking...
Sounds like a hassle.
I'll go and get Kaho.
Ibara? Oh, that girl.
Oh. Chi, you made it!
You're so darn happy.
Fine, gimme my curse.
Please say he didn't!
We're locked in here.
So go ahead and yell.
Please let this work.
Happy New Year to ya!
Are you feeling okay?
Oreki... What are...?
Divine psychic powers?
Yeah. That's possible.
You're a real trooper.
Here, found this, too.
Yeah, about this much?
That's a good question.
How does she know that?
I'll take one of those.
Uh, nah, but it's fine.
That's not very secure.
Hey, what's the matter?
Thank you for saying so!
You know... Forget this.
Hey, Fuku, look at this!
The sash would fall off.
Oh, you know what, Oreki?
Lost children everywhere.
Okay, pick one out, then!
I thought we had options.
Help isn't coming, is it?
Um... Did you say string?
Hotaro! Are you in there?
I'm opening the door now.
I hope it brings you luck.
Excuse us, is anyone here?
You mean we're classmates?
What do you propose we do?
What? There are that many?
The strap from my sandals?
then I might have an idea.
How could that ever happen?
It's New Year's, all right.
What are you guys gonna do?
Then let's head over there.
Someone left this unlocked.
What is she, a wild animal?
That's the fortune he drew.
If there's no other choice,
Hotaro Oreki, tagging along.
No, it's the normal pattern.
Whoa, that purse is amazing!
I'll tag along and help you.
What will happen after that?
It would be a major scandal!
Oh, good, he's walking away.
Let's just hope she gets it.
That's what we'll use, then.
What?! That's not an option!
but that's beside the point.
Okay, I wanna get this right.
A very Happy New Year to you.
I've come to pay my respects.
I do hope you will accept it.
Thanks, I'm glad you like it!
I just had the greatest idea!
Yeah, you're right. Silly me.
She's working as an attendant.
Thank you for your generosity.
No, it missed her, thankfully.
if they were to misunderstand.
We could drop my handkerchief.
Oh, yeah. You're right, I can!
We're done. Help isn't coming.
My wallet should do the trick.
We can't hold out much longer.
Whoa. What's the matter, Fuku?
"Like a rat trapped in a bag?"
That's not really up her alley.
Well, then. Shall we go in now?
I'm his daughter, Eru Chitanda.
May it bring you luck, as well.
I hope that it brings you luck.
He was here earlier in the day.
Here, Oreki, do you wanna play?
Is this really the right place?
Happy New Year to you, as well.
Yes, that's it! Satoshi's here!
The withdrawal from Kanegazaki?
Mis-Happy New Year, my friends.
How did we end up in this state?
May it grow throughout the year.
It was way busier earlier today.
No way! We can't do any of that!
Your purse is just a bag, right?
Never mind, it was a stupid joke.
Thanks, and pardon the intrusion.
That's 'cause they did it for me!
Don't remember asking, but great.
Did something happen around here?
Well, I imagine they'd rush over,
Yeah. One, we kick the door down.
That's Hotaro's wallet, isn't it?
Would taking it off be difficult?
Mayaka, quick! Where is the shed?
Yes, that would be really helpful.
Did you get a good one too, Oreki?
This place... It is a shed, right?
Please don't draw attention to us!
To you it may just be an old shed,
But I think I'd be able to manage.
That's not very nice of you, Oreki.
We don't want it if it isn't fancy.
When did you plan on mentioning it?
Two, we tear down one of the walls.
No, you're right, I guess it's not.
Mis-Happy New Year yourself, buddy.
Oh, so you're Tetsugo's little girl?
Though it really is nothing special.
Oh, that's terrible. Was she burned?
Kaho said to look in the storehouse.
How are we going to get out of here?
It has to have reached Ibara by now,
It would be kind of hard, I suppose.
Hello, this is Eru Chitanda speaking.
Well, uh... It's nothing super fancy.
A new year's fortune sounds like fun.
It's just... You can't yell for help.
Sorry, Chitanda, this may be awkward.
So this is a genuine shrine priestess?
You're in class 1-B, isn't that right?
Let's hurry up and get this over with.
But you wouldn't be too happy about it
Hey, have you seen Eru, by any chance?
Hotaro drew bad luck and it came true.
Fifty centimeters is more than enough.
We could use the obijime from my sash.
I'm not making anything up, I promise.
"The Case of the Homemade Chocolates."
Thinking what? Is there something else?
I'm excited to continue our friendship.
Please, come in. Make yourself at home.
Look at your kimono! It's so beautiful!
He went home to watch some drama on TV.
Really well. I have great night vision.
But enough about me, how was your show?
Sadly, I'm wearing boots with no laces.
his brother-in-law, Azai, betrayed him.
Happy New Year and luck to you, as well.
No. It's just as much my fault as yours.
It looks like someone's coming this way!
I always feel so awkward around Jumonji.
Seems like yours might be the real deal.
Do you have any plans for New Years' Day?
I wanted to show off this outfit tonight!
So this must be how the other half lives.
Four, we bust a hole through the ceiling.
It feels like it's getting chillier, too.
I thought Fukube was coming with you guys.
That hairstyle looks really pretty on you!
I've never seen one so fancy in real life!
You're really that excited by my bad luck?
I guess I just don't understand her world.
I want to draw one of those fortunes, too.
Can't use that. We need your purse intact.
We were on the verge of freezing to death.
Why don't we start by offering our prayers?
and I can understand if it's bothering you.
All right. Well... I'm gonna yell for help.
It must be pretty hard to work in the cold.
but it seems that alone isn't gonna cut it.
All right! Now it's time to execute plan B.
Looks like that moron must have dropped it.
It's a coat that you wear over your kimono.
It isn't selfish. It's your responsibility.
Okay, but what are you going to do with it?
Hotaro, Chitanda! Don't worry, here I come!
I don't think I've heard that story before.
He should be back in a little while, though.
Except for that fortune, his wallet's empty.
Fukube should have made it back by now, too.
Oh, what about the drawstring from my purse?
Then why don't we use one of your shoelaces?
Well, is there any other string around here?
and why's this old string tied to the purse?
Ibara mentioned earlier that any time someone
They're serving hot sweet saké at the office.
This is Kaho Jumonji. She's also in class 1-B.
What was it called? Dark Clouds: Odani Castle?
Oh, I'm sorry, Eru. I forgot to offer you tea.
Sorry about that, Oreki, it just dawned on me.
This is all because I made one stupid mistake.
I am only here tonight to represent my father.
So, a handkerchief, a wallet, and now a purse?
What in the world is going on with those guys,
Please, Oreki. It's not your place to say that.
You could call it a shed or maybe even a shack.
I can't believe we didn't think of that before.
It's a parishioner volunteer making his rounds.
He's going to drop it off at the shrine office.
What were you up to today? Anything interesting?
I really hope there's a light in here, at least.
And anyway, it's not our fault we got locked in.
If it were another night, it might be different,
But desperate times call for desperate measures.
Oh, yes, may it continue to flourish and prosper.
The real hassle was running around all day today.
So Ibara, what do they have you selling in there?
I think I remember seeing it by the Inari statue.
All of those parishioners... They know my family.
Look, Fuku, does this handkerchief look familiar?
I can manage whatever gossip might arise from it.
I don't know much about kimonos, so bear with me.
Mayaka said she got a job there over the holidays.
Well, right now, Ibara is in charge of lost items.
I just got here, so I haven't run into anyone yet.
The stove is on in the great hall, if you're cold.
I think I remember seeing a flag outside the shed.
This is definitely Chi's purse, no doubt about it!
to send the message that she was a "rat in a bag."
This will take you right to the back of the kiosks.
I'll be getting out of here in about an hour or so.
I still think it's going to be a really great year.
You think that she could have meant farther inside?
Chitanda, do you happen to have any kind of string?
Chitanda, I need to borrow your purse for a minute.
It's over that way, right next to the Inari statue.
The phrase was coined at a famous historical event.
When Nobunaga was laying siege to the Asakura clan,
It's not a big deal or anything, I just had an idea.
Running around bringing New Year's gifts to priests?
Is she still embarrassed about her attendant outfit?
I don't know how much of the story is actually true,
Knowing how his mind works, he'll get what it means.
Look, we'll only shout out for help as a last resort.
I guess a lot of people like to get dressed up for it.
Oh, don't scare him like that. Please accept our gift.
And to make matters worse, it's been emptied out, too.
They're messing with me, and I freaked out like a dork.
There's nothing but a wall to the left, where she said.
The parishioners said they found this by the shed, too!
You know the expression, "like a rat trapped in a bag?"
But that doesn't make much sense, if you think about it.
We'd like to see Mayaka Ibara. Do you know where she is?
The parishioners who volunteer are a little overzealous,
If someone comes in to get something and finds us alone,
Three, we dig a tunnel to the outside through the floor.
I'm pretty sure Mayaka has seen me use it several times.
Okay, Chitanda, drop your handkerchief through the hole.
for the rest of the year, which is completely ridiculous.
I got in some good practice on my hermit crab impression.
On behalf of Tetsugo Chitanda and the rest of our family,
I have brought a bottle of saké as a gift from my father.
I'm about to scream as loud as I can, so cover your ears.
I didn't bring my phone with me. We'll have to use yours.
I thought that our handkerchief plan would work for sure,
I guess my hanky didn't leave a strong enough impression.
I'm regretting the decision not to wear my haori, though.
Well, is there anything else I can do to be of assistance?
I'm willing to bet this is Hotaro's bad luck hard at work.
so if anything at all gets
found, they bring it right here.
unbar the door, and we'd be
free to finish what we started.
Well, we can't take the door
off its hinges from this side.
Yeah, could you bring in some
saké lees from the storehouse?
Until then, let's brainstorm
for anything else we could try.
but it's still one of the
Arekusu shrine's sacred buildings!
You've probably heard of the
Battle of Anegawa, haven't you?
Sorry I can't show you around,
but you can go in on your own.
I really wish I had worn a
trenchcoat myself right about now.
Not to be rude, but right now
I am a little bit more concerned
Great! Well, do you want to
visit the Arekusu Shrine that day?
One of the part-timers knocked
over some pots and made a mess.
It looks a lot like one that
Chi has, but I'm not really sure.
That doesn't give me an excuse
to make you suffer for it, too.
Not so fast! There's no way I'd
let you cook dressed like that!
not making a peep, they're
definitely gonna get the wrong idea.
about our current predicament
than I am about the next 364 days.
I kind of feel like wearing my
kimono, but I'm a little nervous.
Oh, my family doesn't have a
storehouse, so I just got confused!
Because... If someone out there
hears and comes to let us out...
but tonight would be the worst
possible time for them to find us.
We can't move the bar, call out,
or take the door off its hinges,
I've never known anyone who got
a bad luck fortune before tonight!
When you see Chitanda in a little
while, you can ask her about it.
May I only expend a moderate
amount of energy for this entire year.
but she hasn't skipped out on
work to come investigate or anything.
And from what I can tell, it looks
like he found a cell phone strap.
I'd rather risk my reputation than
risk either of us catching a cold.
But how would it look when they
opened the door and found us together?
Our cell phones! We can just shoot
them a text and they'll let us out!
It's convenient that you might know
who the owner is, don't you think?
I appreciate you indulging my
selfish request for as long as you have.
And I look forward to happy relations
with you in the coming year, too.
So we can drop something out there
that obviously belongs to one of us.
If you took off the obijime, would
the rest of the kimono hold up okay?
I'd say it's mostly because you
picked an unlucky fortune, wouldn't you?
I also give change, and it's the
lost and found for kids and belongings.
I spent all morning and afternoon
visiting relatives and paying respects.
I'm not allowed to wear the ones
with long sleeves until I go to college.
Fukube said that it sounds like fun
and that he'll be joining us, as well.
The only people here who wouldn't
jump to conclusions are Kaho and Mayaka.
I think we'll just stay in the main
hall area and wait for you to get done.
There's a legendary story that happened
right before that; have you heard it?
drops something of value, the parishioners
bring it over to the shrine office.
Once we get that, I have a sure-fire
way of alerting Satoshi to our situation.
I thought this would just be a quick
errand, but it's turning out to be a pain.
Listen, Chitanda, do you think it'd be
okay to break open the wall just a little?
Otherwise, it would mean that if you took
New Year's Day off, then you would be off
I don't know. Mayaka's the one who talked
to him about coming here with us tonight.
Nobunaga's sister, Oichi, sent a bean bag
tied up at both ends to him in the field,
They're right to your left when you walk
in, so you should be able to recognize them.
but there are still four avenues of escape
we haven't explored yet, so don't give up.
If we could somehow convey our current
predicament to her, she would come let us out!
It was an absolute masterpiece! I couldn't
have asked for a better start to the year!
I remembered that the mikoshi storage room
is right next to the shrine office, though.
Now we have to whip up a ton of dumpling
soup and sweet saké on the fly for the guests.
I didn't know you didn't have a cell phone,
and that's why I said not to shout for help.
It just so happens that Satoshi and I both
saw that episode play out on a TV show today.
When you tie off the opening and the bottom,
that closes up all the contents inside of it.
When they bring it to her, she would recognize it
and pay closer attention to it than other things.
I just blanked for a few minutes on who to call,
but when it dawned on me, it didn't matter anymore.
If you don't mind my asking, how are you going to
get help from Fukube using a little bit of string?
Isn't there a superstition that whatever you do on
New Year's Day, you'll end up doing all year long?
Whether or not she makes the connection to the shed
is the hard part, so we'll need all the luck we can get.
My family does business with the priests here, so I
wanted to bring them a New Year's present from my father.
If they came to rescue us, they would recognize me, and
if they saw us in here together, they would misunderstand!