No.
Oh.
Hm?
Yes.
Yes?
I...
Fine.
Sono!
Yeah.
Sure.
Here.
Yeah.
'Kay.
Right.
Hmm...
Oreki.
I see.
Right!
Wow...
I see.
Oreki.
Oreki!
I see.
Wait...
Thanks.
Gotcha.
Hotaro!
Oh. Yes.
You did?
Nakatake!
The kids?
Tanimoto!
Yes, sir?
Yes, sir.
Tanimoto.
Yes, sir?
Yes, sir.
Aw, crap.
Could be.
Oh, yeah?
It's fine.
Fantastic!
Oh. Sorry.
'Scuse me.
So, Oreki.
Uh... yes?
Sincerely.
From whom?
Excuse me.
Who knows?
Yes, I am.
Oh, Oreki.
Um, Oreki?
Hey, Hanai.
Call Murai.
Yes, it is.
That's all.
Hey, Hanai,
Not good...
I couldn't.
And he's...
Hey, Oreki.
Anyone here?
Who are you?
In the hall.
That's true.
That's good.
Huh... Uh...
Interesting.
It suits me.
But still...
That's right.
I don't know.
Man, shut up.
That's right!
Good for you.
By the way...
The newspaper.
Oreki, was it?
It's freezing.
Main building.
Did he really?
Will that work?
Got it covered.
Kinda sad, huh?
Yeah, for what?
You have? Good.
Oreki residence.
Dolls' Festival?
Ah, yes, I know.
Are the dolls...
Right away, sir.
Oh. I guess not.
That's for sure.
Mm-hmm. I heard.
Oh, okay, right.
That's for sure.
Oh. Uh, nothing.
My name is Oreki.
The living dolls?
What did you say?
This is not good!
Oh. Hello, Oreki.
What I mean is...
Okay, good to go?
Well, I know him.
That makes sense.
What do you mean?
It's fascinating.
Yes, that's right.
Excuse me, mister.
Yeah, you're fine.
Then why did they?
No dolls for them?
Are you listening?
Oh, isn't that...?
Well, not too bad.
What do you think?
Oh, good, so do I.
Yes, I believe so.
Ah, so that's why.
I love this place.
Your what? Parasol?
What does she want?
Oreki, is that you?
What? What's wrong?
Ready, set, reveal!
For crying out loud.
They need more time.
All right, everyone,
That's a long story.
Oh, the cherry tree!
1:00 is way too late!
Have them move it up!
I think that's Irisu.
I can't see Chitanda.
Today was just awful!
All right. I'll do it.
So the dolls can walk?
As far as I know, yes.
I can't relax in here.
It's my pleasure, sir.
Never mind the reason.
Please tell them that.
Oh. Hey, there, Irisu.
Don't do that, please.
Well, I chose science.
But it's already April.
It's too late for that.
Is it anything serious?
That's all she told me.
What would happen then?
I wouldn't go that far.
I see two ways, really.
No. It's spring, silly.
Geez, for the love of...
But not everyone agrees.
Well, what do you think?
Man, that was fantastic!
Do you know what it was?
I wouldn't call it that.
I know it's short notice,
Where should I put these?
And, the finishing touch.
I just... I have to know.
Will that cover it, Hanai?
What are you waiting for?!
I can't see how she looks.
For the Valentine's thing.
How's it been going since?
That's a frivolous motive.
I'm not sure what you mean.
Hey, Nakatake, are we good?
I delegated it to the maid.
I didn't think it mattered.
Yes. That's me. What is it?
That is Chitanda, isn't it?
What is the matter with me?
Looking down so demurely...
You just have to know, huh?
Ah, so that was a big deal.
You may have a point there.
We're good. It's on the way.
Are you positive about this?
What's he glaring at me for?
Tanimoto! This falls on you!
Dressed up so beautifully...
Yeah, you're a real trooper.
Head upstream along the brook
Well, I didn't ask them that.
I'm not sure about it either.
So is that the whole message?
Oreki, I wanted to thank you.
Weren't you the emperor doll?
I've been obsessing about it,
Hanai, sir! Telephone for you.
What's going on with the saké?
You did follow up, didn't you?
Oh, I chose lit. Seemed right.
I know this is where I belong.
Hello, my name is Hotaro Oreki.
We're shorthanded, but still...
I came back home just for this.
For real, it was wasted on you.
Fine, keep running your mouths.
They do this every year, right?
Which is why you chose science?
It's starting to get cold, huh?
You won't be able to cross back.
Sorry I can't come out and talk.
Okay, then that's what we'll do.
Yes, Toji bridge. Did I stutter?
has encountered a deadly threat.
And that's where you stepped in.
If I manage to get into college,
Just look at all of this, Oreki.
Is it okay if I ride across here?
Hey. Where are the spare banners?
What if they took the same route,
Start getting things ready to go!
I'm rethinking this entire thing.
He helped me get into my costume.
Walk with all the dolls, you mean?
You sure are a stalwart young man.
Well... I reminded Murai about it.
So then what do you propose we do?
There's an issue at Chokyu bridge.
Don't worry, they will understand.
We're thinking of the same person?
You mean someone holds it for them?
They're not really dolls, are they?
We appreciate your help, young man.
Not that, silly, the Chokyu bridge!
Yeah, and I thought that was weird.
Oh, you came to take Hazawa's place?
Murai is in charge of that now, sir.
then crossing over to the west side?
There's not much time, so talk fast.
My philosophy of energy conservation
If I could see her from the front...
They were so gorgeous, weren't they?
I snapped at him for that, you know.
You'd be willing to carry my parasol.
This shrine goes by the old calendar.
The dolls are just girls in costumes.
We're about to start working, though.
What's the problem with construction?
I'm curious: why did you suspect him?
By the way what? Finish that thought.
I wonder if this is how Satoshi felt.
I'm supposed to be carrying a parasol.
First time I've ever been called that.
We have to deal with this immediately.
They could just stay on the east bank.
Well, for one, they altered the route.
Doing that took us to the Toji bridge.
Afraid to spoil it by saying too much.
I'm sorry about that. Come right on in.
I gave it to Nakatake 'cause it rhymed.
He assured me he would take care of it.
I'm not quite finished getting dressed.
Can you fill me in as much as possible?
That's fine with me, but write on what?
Yes, and it was blooming out of season.
what channels to use to make that call.
Oh, over in the hall, if you don't mind.
Hey, Hanai, who's in charge of the saké?
They told me that it'll be here at 1:00.
It's true! They've resumed construction!
I guess it does, sure, but I don't know.
The business with Nakagawa Construction!
Well, yeah, I do have a suspect in mind.
And you're saying that was Konari's son?
of a little community north of Kamiyama.
with the goal of wasting nothing at all.
I just have to stand next to them, right?
Plus, if someone gets hurt, we're liable.
You're right, that's an odd thing to say.
However, a "rare sight" did happen today.
I'm not depressed about coming back here.
I didn't explain that very clearly, did I?
Well, no, you have to walk alongside them.
I guess Chitanda didn't tell you about me?
You just relax here until we send for you.
Tanimoto, is the Chokyu bridge good to go?
Yeah, but I couldn't fit into the costume.
I'm still gonna come back here eventually.
What about the parishioner representatives?
Is there someone here by the name of Oreki?
we'll take a detour across the Toji bridge.
Where are Chitanda and the other dolls now?
And in this one, I'm just the emperor doll.
I was dying to ask about it the whole time.
This is embarrassing enough for me as it is.
I must say, that was an excellent retelling.
If I'm in the parade, I can't see it, right?
That is what I'd call a "rare sight to see."
without thinking twice about their feelings.
when I saw how I was driving everyone crazy.
The procession is set to cross Chokyu bridge.
The workers told me a similar story just now.
That's great for the people on the east side,
Chitanda's daughter asked me to come get you.
I called you back here to find out what's up.
I'm gonna go get another one of these things.
I haven't had a chance to tell you until now.
Are you a moron?! The parade is over at 12:30!
Oh, you must be that kid Chitanda recommended.
Something has gone kind of haywire, hasn't it?
I was asked to be a replacement parasol-bearer.
but doubled back instead of crossing the river?
Oreki, can I ask you to relay a message for me?
It's not very often that I really lay into him.
I've been forced to hold it in this whole time!
Okay, then who would have made that phone call?
What if I were to take on that task for myself?
You mean it?! I can't thank you enough for this!
and take the Chokyu bridge past the cherry tree.
The TV crew is already here and set up to shoot.
A lot of it sounds a bit suspect, if you ask me.
would be a major source of contention, even now.
No. It's Mizunashi Shrine's Living Doll Festival.
I'm sorry that a stranger like me has to intrude.
Then what if they go down to the bridge and back,
We could have them cross over at the Toji bridge.
Besides, this kind of procession is a rare sight.
They said something about purging their impurity.
In that situation, I had a specific role to play.
There's nothing here but the water and the earth.
I really hope you're mistaken about this one, kid.
No, there has to be some kind of misunderstanding!
but what about all the folks gathered on the west?
then cross over here and then go up the west side?
but since I had a part to play, I couldn't let on.
Everyone was running around like crazy here today.
No wonder Satoshi calls your family "prestigious."
I just felt compelled to share it with you, Oreki.
Wow. That cherry tree. It's blooming out of season.
but I wouldn't dismiss it as insignificant, either.
Did Chitanda really not know there was construction?
I'll try my very best to keep out of everyone's way.
I refuse to do something that ridiculous on live TV.
And I don't even believe it has very much potential.
but do you have any plans for the day after tomorrow?
Scratch that, get Nakagawa Construction on the phone.
He specifically told them not to start working today.
Then what about going halfway to the bridge and back,
That was what finally calmed all the chaos, you know.
There were lots of disputes over water and territory.
I don't think it's something grandiose or monumental,
It's actually quite the contrary, as a matter of fact.
It would mean the world to me if you could help us out.
Actually, they resumed construction a little while ago.
I hate to do this, but take the truck and go make sure.
the cameraman wants to know where he should shoot from.
Chitanda and Irisu's elegance was absolutely unmatched!
And speaking of those, I heard about the Chokyu bridge.
Apparently, his lifelong dream is to be a photographer.
Never mind that. What about the business this afternoon?
Thanks a lot for coming all the way here to help us out.
So, um, weren't you originally slated to take over here?
It may seem kind of trivial, but hear me out, would you?
The people who live here will slowly grow old and tired.
We already talked with Takahashi in the traffic division!
We'd better find a way to reroute and avoid it altogether.
The north half was our village, and the south was another.
Shame we had to bother an
outsider to carry a damn parasol.
If I do anything to offend,
please let me know immediately.
Well, do you know if they've
halted construction, at least?
So it's been proposed that we
cross at Toji bridge instead.
Oh, Konari's son does have
brown hair, as a matter of fact.
If they cross at the Toji
bridge, then back via Kaya bridge,
It's not the most beautiful
place in the world by any means.
We'd only get to see it by
taking the route we ended up with.
But couple that with your
theory, and I am totally convinced.
Good morning. It's Chitanda.
Sorry to bother you on a day off.
it only ends up being slightly
longer than the original route.
And since I have no stake in
any of this, I won't mislead you.
I'm sure he just wanted to get
a photo of such a "rare sight."
That was a lesson that I learned
during the cultural festival,
I'm positive that Murai called
the construction office earlier!
If he's from here, why would
this procession be so rare to him?
He is going to vocational school
to study it, as far as I know.
I will speak to the other shrine's
priest about this right away.
All I did was act as a liaison
between the north and south sides
I've given a lot of thought to
how I might best be able to do it.
Ultimately, I think the former is
the more appropriate path for me.
By the way, buddy, that outfit
did not suit you at all, just saying.
Walking twice the length of the
current route is out of the question.
Oreki, please! I'd appreciate it
if you'd stop saying "dolls" so much.
I am also going to have my father
call the parishioner representative.
You must have drawn up some conclusion
about everything that happened.
So, Oreki... What did you choose
for your second year? Science or lit?
But who knows what he was really
thinking. Why did you suspect him too?
The spectacle of a parade of living
dolls passing under cherry blossoms?
A long time ago, this area was
divided into two halves: north and south.
No matter where life takes me, in
the end, my place will always be here.
I don't think I have the skillset
needed to manage a bunch of employees.
I've been participating as one of
the living dolls for the past few years.
There's gotta be a way to get them
to halt construction before the parade.
As far as the managerial perspective
that you determined wasn't for you...
I thought you'd be the first person
to try his hand at solving the mystery.
You're going to be carrying a parasol
for Chitanda's daughter, is that right?
Yeah, I definitely don't think you're
cut out for the latter path, no offense.
They can't find anyone who fits into his
costume, but you guys are the same size.
Why don't we write it down and reveal
our theories to each other at the same time?
Remember in my dressing room when I
mentioned contacting the other shrine's priest?
They wanted to let them know ahead of time,
but there aren't many people who even know
Once I talked to the other side, we were
free to go that far south with peace of mind.
As the daughter of the Chitanda family, I
want to fulfill the role I was born to play.
When the others heard that, for some odd
reason they started acting weird and scowling.
I'm only asking because one of the parasol
holders had a freak accident and can't do it.
First of all, it seems pretty clear that they
got a call saying to come to work today, right?
One of those is to help us all prosper by
developing a commodity that's extremely marketable.
Konari's son is the only person around here who
would put so many people through all that stress
And though that was so long ago, for a solemn
ritual like this, crossing over without permission
There was only one person who seemed totally
sure we wouldn't be able to cross the Chokyu bridge.
The other way would be to make our production
more efficient, working from a managerial standpoint,
I do know they got a call the day before yesterday
to go ahead as planned, though, so maybe that's why.
Let me try again. The shrine near my house is hosting a
Dolls' Festival the day after tomorrow and we need help.
He told me that he came back home just for this, and he
said that this kind of procession is a rare sight to see.
Listen, I know it's kind of rude to ask you this out of
the blue, so no pressure, but I was wondering, well, if...