Oh.
Hm?
Wow.
Yep!
Yes?
Yes!
Yes.
Here.
What?
Well?
Yeah.
Later.
Great!
Right!
Great.
Hmm...
Right!
Well...
You do?
Hold on!
...this.
Ibara...
Hi, Chi.
Nothing.
Satoshi.
Anyway...
Oh, yeah?
This one!
Now what?
I mean...
Oh, well.
Second...
Seriously?
Hey, wait!
Hold on...
Way to go!
What's up?
Next time:
Yo, Fukube!
Aw, bummer.
Hey, there!
Later, bro!
Swallow it.
Fine, then.
All right.
Whoop-sies!
Oh, Mayaka!
Well, then.
'Bout what?
Well, uh...
Interesting.
It's no use.
What's that?
Pretty much.
There it is.
But I can't!
Gym clothes?
She's what?!
There's not.
Oh! Satoshi!
Four. Three.
Same for you.
Check it out!
You're here?!
It's a manga?
Damn it, Sis.
See you then!
I'm all done.
That's right.
How 'bout it?
What's wrong?
There's this.
Let me see...
Oh, excuse me!
Cooking Club .
Keyword, "if."
Hi. Guess I am.
That's awesome!
First of all...
This is so good.
Right! Let's go!
You had to know!
Listen, Oreki...
Gardening Club .
Lastly, seventh.
A.B.C. Murders ,
Hi, hello there.
Oh... right! Me!
Light Music Club?
Anshinin Takuha."
Nice to meet you.
It's no big deal.
Sorry, President.
So I was correct!
Classic Lit Club.
Third question...
All right, Jumoji.
I see. Well, then.
"Anshinin Takuha"?
I'm Eru Chitanda--
What's the matter?
I kind of need it.
What do you think?
Right. I remember.
How do we proceed?
She seems familiar.
least of all to me.
Why did he have it?
This is incredible!
That's a mere blip.
You mean like this?
Those come to mind.
On in five seconds.
Hey, guys. I'm back.
Great! Hi, Chitanda.
But... I've seen it.
I... I have to know!
I'm so sorry, Ibara.
At least I hope not.
Oh. It's about this!
Oh. I had to change.
I need it right now.
Yes, please tell us.
Yeah. Good question.
A Corpse by Evening .
Turned out well, huh?
Come on. Out with it.
Not fair! Okay, fine.
Yeah, okay. Go ahead.
He's right about that.
Did I hear that right?
How did you know that?
That's not my problem.
We meet again, Tanabe.
We solved the mystery!
Wait... What the heck?
Oh, wow. Good for you.
Isn't that a surprise?
The Light Music Club .
But it's not possible!
The thief skipped "ku."
So, how can I help you?
It was the same person!
Seriously, who is that?
It's a place in Kyushu.
I'm gonna head back in.
That doesn't make sense.
That's Saturday for you.
The Kudryavka Sequence ?
Mm-hmm. I had to change.
So the question becomes:
The Kudryavka Sequence .
So why keep it a secret?
Nothing's happening here.
The Kudryavka Sequence ."
Wow, Chi, that's amazing!
Would you really do that?
Let's hear this lewdness.
Is that just coincidence?
"The Kudryavka Sequence."
Took one of their strings.
Thanks, I won't take long!
I want to compare the two!
It was Muneyoshi Kugayama.
Should I know who that is?
So... it's "obscene," huh?
I'm just not convinced yet.
Not them. Light Music Club.
What's your opinion, Oreki?
Well... very. Oddly enough.
Ah. That would be Kugayama.
So, was it the same person?
We even found out his name!
being sold at the festival?
Is that what you're saying?
I hope I'm wrong about that.
Well, if I do say so myself,
Yeah, you're right. It does.
Hey, are you busy right now?
No, I'm not busy, what's up?
Next to the conference room!
Thanks, I'm glad to hear it!
Getting Around at Kanyasai .
The Light Music Club got hit.
Thank you for your patronage.
What's that supposed to mean?
It's on the tip of my tongue!
Thank you. Have a lovely day!
No, I haven't. I promise you!
Something you'd like to share?
The timing couldn't be better!
Thanks for watching the store.
Where did you see this poster?
Yeah, of course! Bonus points!
The student council president.
It's not so much that, either.
Mm-hmm. Let's hear them, then.
Why choose that in particular?
I wanna help Chitanda prepare.
This is boring. I'm outta here.
Don't worry about me! I'm fine.
My head-on approach didn't work.
Yeah, that's right. Who are you?
I really didn't mean to do that.
Great! Then you have to tell us!
Right. Bait... I like that idea.
I didn't think you would show up!
her dear little brother is doing?
I think it turned out very well."
Credit where it's due, you know?"
We meet at 12 noon in the studio!
I hope you can manage without me.
It was lucky that I ran into you!
We're really sorry to bother you,
It was at the Cooking Club event.
and The Murder of Roger Ackroyd .
At this year's Cultural Festival,
You're a little late this morning.
My sister just brought this to me.
I'm 99% sure it's the same person.
Hello. You're from the... hold on.
We couldn't have asked for better.
I need to borrow you for a second.
Hey, is that true? Tell us, Oreki!
I'm looking forward to it, Hotaro.
That reminds me. I picked this up.
What's wrong, phantom thief Jumoji?
But Chitanda would stand in my way.
There are over a thousand suspects.
I'd say, And Then There Were None ,
Then Murder on the Orient Express ,
And Then There Were None , instead.
Still, why would he skip over "ku?"
I have high hopes for this, Hotaro.
If you're gonna strike, bring it on!
You're sure that's good information?
"We picked another foreboding name."
I don't know what "Kudryavka" means,
I am so glad you were actually here!
The broadcast starts at 12:30 sharp.
Your eyes are playing tricks on you.
No way. There's no doubt in my mind.
What do you mean, "Anshinin Takuha?"
That's meant to be read as, "Ajimu."
One of Christie's most famous works.
the crime must not have happened yet.
You can blame the Warashibe protocol.
This is some fine artwork right here.
I now know the author and the artist!
Sorry to drag you out here with this.
No worries. Doesn't bother me at all.
Is Jumoji's next target the Quiz Club?
Were you scared off by all the people?
I might be a bit out of my depth here.
so she brought another ten down there.
"The next story is going to be called:
You're the Classic Lit Club president!
Have you had some kind of realization?
Yeah, man. This scene's over. I'm gone.
I have to go back to the drawing board.
It doesn't really suit you, little bro.
Just let me look at another page, okay?
Would you like to find out who drew it?
I hope this lucky streak keeps rolling.
No one asked you to share your hunches!
Wouldn't you say "stolen," or, "taken?"
I don't think this is all just for fun.
I'm your favorite DJ, Yasukuni Yoshino.
I'm so happy to be here talking to you!
they must have kicked it into high gear.
Is that right? Did he hit the Quiz Club?
Then I sold nine more just this morning.
No. I haven't discovered anything there.
I didn't have much to do with it at all."
I couldn't have planned it better myself!
Have there been any further developments?
Just make sure you bring it back quickly.
What? That's crazy! Where did you get it?
It's absolutely beautiful! A masterpiece!
My thoughts were at a standstill, anyway.
I wonder if I've met her somewhere before.
When they sell, they sell out, don't they?
I'm starting to have some hope about this.
I was literally just on my way to see you!
I think we should start over from scratch.
He's all engrossed with that doujin manga;
He said that his sister brought it to him.
It does have to do with the Jumoji affair.
Well, Kudryavka was a nickname for the dog
We go live when he gives us the cue, okay?
he's had his head buried in it for a while.
Why the gym clothes? What about Manga Club?
Oh. So you know something about this manga?
That's my hunch, but I haven't decided yet.
When it comes to high gear, I can't be beat.
Do you think... I could borrow it for a bit?
is Classic Lit Club president, Eru Chitanda!
Your pen turned into this little hand mirror.
The way they handle the ears is unmistakable.
I will let the creators toot their own horns."
but the word "sequence" captures my attention.
I would be honored to be a guest on your show!
Yeah, that's cool, but give me a little while.
Proofed manuscripts? Koryogenko fits the bill.
He'll be tickled when I tell him you said that.
If this is already up this early in the morning,
You and I have said we think that work is either
There are a number of ways to pull that one off.
It's not the only thing that lists all the clubs.
You mean you traded my pen and ended up with that?
Also, which "one of Christie's most famous works?"
He stole gen , a string from the Light Music Club.
You've figured something out, haven't you, Hotaro?
I just need to gather my thoughts a little better.
And Then There Were None , or The A.B.C. Murders .
At least, the executive committee hasn't been told.
Satoshi, there's a specific reason he's doing this.
Hmph. That dirty thief Jumoji made a fool out of us.
I borrowed it from Oreki. He was reading it earlier.
For Ibara to say that openly, it must be remarkable.
It's obscene. That's why I left you out of it. Okay?
Look, it's not like I don't have any ideas about it.
That's simple: he did it to keep from being noticed.
I'll take it off your hands, and in return you get...
Chitanda, this is really not the time for that stuff.
Sixth question, and no doubt the weirdest one of all:
With that violent image in mind, I think I would say,
A special broadcast of Yasukuni Yoshino's Radio Beat!
The 20 copies Chitanda gave to Irisu are already gone,
Maybe I'll get the chance to chat with them in person!
"How can you manage to stand out with so little time?"
Why does he leave a calling card at all of his crimes?
Lit Club or the Industrial Arts Club will be hit next.
It's the last day of the festival: the moment of truth.
This whole time I thought it was pronounced "Rikuyama."
Is that information crucial to surviving my daily life?
I'm curious, and I want to be in the loop about things.
With me on this, the last day of the Cultural Festival,
It's gonna be hard to keep Jumoji at large at this rate.
I see you've decided to take on the easy work, as usual.
"Our writer, A, is considering turning the writing style
Hey, Oreki. Would you mind letting me borrow this manga?
Mayaka, how familiar are you with this particular manga?
the Soviets shot into space, but she never made it back.
You're pretty determined if you're staking out this early.
If I can't catch him in the act, then how can I catch him?
completely on its ear and delving into the mystery genre."
For some reason, that picture looks really familiar to me.
It's khaki, so even if it stains, it won't show up anyway.
First and foremost, guests are only allotted five minutes.
There are several other clubs that start with "E" and "O."
Jumoji's adaptability is more
sophisticated than I thought.
Our goal of selling all these
copies just got within reach!
and I have a feeling that they
might be pretty significant.
Fourth, why does he always
leave a Kanyasai guidebook, too?
Answering that could help us
figure out whether the Classic
Now Chitanda's got that
insatiably curious look in her eyes!
We just assumed that because
of the way he signed his notes.
And that assumption has since
been challenged by new events.
I'd think they would use, The
A.B.C. Murders , wouldn't you?
What do you think of the way A
Corpse by Evening turned out?"
then see if there's any room
for a few twists here and there."
Why does he keep saying that
the missing items have been lost?
Are you implying the manga has
something to do with this case?
I guess I'm saying I don't
think they're completely unrelated.
Why steal something from them
when their event is already over?
Of course, all I did was help
out with some of the backgrounds.
Pardon, but are you Yoshino,
the Broadcasting Club's president?
I just have a few problems I
can't seem to wrap my head around,
Why did he decide to skip over
"ku," and hit "ke" next instead?
I'm going to see if there's
anything in this stuff you gave me.
You need to change out of your
rainbow parakeet costume, though.
What? You mean Muneyoshi Kugayama?
The student council president?
But I'm not convinced it's a good
enough plan to sell all of them.
Would you like to be a guest on
our radio show today during lunch?
It looks similar to a poster I
saw outside of the conference room!
The same. I had to badger him a
bit to convince him, but he caved.
It's not even like I have anything
earth-shattering to talk about.
All right. Come on, Hotaro, that's
enough messing around for today.
So, then, are you saying this
isn't about the Jumoji matter at all?
Now, let me coach you through the
basics of giving a good interview.
If she knew what I was trying to
do, she'd definitely be against it.
that was going to be a take on one
of "Christie's most famous works."
Satoshi, do you know if there's a
manga called, The Kudryavka Sequence
Judging by the fact that there are
this many amateur detectives around,
It's one of my favorites. I bought
it at last year's cultural festival.
What do you think when you hear,
"one of Christie's most famous works?"
I guess Anshinin Takuha is just the
name they adopted for the whole team?
"Okay, I look forward to seeing you
next year during the Kanyasai season!
Fifth, why'd he choose to target the
Cooking Club and the Gardening Club?
If you don't believe me, then why
don't you just investigate for yourself?
Well, since we're only speculating,
we don't have to pin it down just yet.
A Corpse by Evening came out at last
year's Cultural Festival, apparently.
causing an uproar at the festival
with as little interference as possible.
What, you're not grateful that your
big sister cares enough to come see how
You really better not have just laid
a bunch of work down on my feet again.
Tell Chitanda to have some "ko" items
out somewhere they'd be easy to find.
The idea to use Jumoji to sell copies
of Hyouka isn't necessarily a bad one.
I think the style's identical, but I
need an expert opinion! I have to know!
"I think it's kind of extraordinary for
a maiden effort, but that's my opinion.
Normally, I would try to get unstuck by
talking everything out with these guys.
Especially since the Cooking Club's
usually called the Ryori Club, not Oryori .
Whether you decide to spend your valuable
time reading it is entirely up to you.
I believe I'm finally beginning to piece
together what you're getting at, Hotaro.
"It's not even as though every single
one of us is in the Manga Club or anything."
When we decided to try making a manga of
our own, this is the story that emerged."
but we're curious: Could you tell us who
drew that poster on the wall right there?
What's the evidence that he's stealing
ten specific items from ten different clubs?
I also think Mayaka would have mentioned
it to us if the Manga Club was selling it.
In the afterword, there was an announcement
that they would write a manga this year
Did you discover some hidden link between
the clubs that have already fallen victim?
Then, did you find some mistake in Jumoji's
methods that might lead us to an answer?
"We have already started working on
something new with next year's Kanyasai in mind."
"The title has already been chosen, so I
suppose I'll go ahead and announce it here."
"Now, keep in mind: We have no intention of
breaking up the team after just one title."
"If you really enjoy the finished product,
the credit goes to the author and the artist,
Kugayama did the artwork, but the story
itself was written by someone named Anjo Haruna.
"The word on the street is that they plan to
take on one of Christie's most famous works,
The pronunciation is written in Romanized
text right here on the cover, next to the name.
"I also want the reader to decide for
themselves, without me putting ideas in their heads."
How are we ever supposed to identify the
culprit without finding any real leads or mistakes?
events similar to The A.B.C. Murders are
taking place, albeit on a much less sinister scale.
"We all just like manga a lot, and really hit it
off when we would get together to talk about it.
Oh, yeah! I almost forgot! The Broadcasting Club
is having me as a guest on their lunchtime show!
The Global Action Club was crawling with civilians,
and it would've made the crime too difficult.
So that means this Kugayama guy is the artist of
the Anshinin Takuha group who created that manga?
If someone were to use one of them as the basis
for a manga with the title The Kudryavka Sequence ,
I think this Jumoji character is just trying to
carry on with his little caper for as long as he can,
I think interviewing the president of the club that's
sure to be Jumoji's final target would be a huge hit.
In other words, you think the key to solving the Jumoji
case is contained in the end of " A Corpse by Evening ."
I saw a poster promoting the Cultural Festival, and I'm
certain that whoever drew this manga also drew the poster!