Hm?
Huh?
Yes.
Hey!
Okay.
'Kay.
Hmph.
Yeah.
Okay.
What?
Right.
Sorry.
Right!
Great!
But...
Right.
Gotcha.
Hyouka?
A favor?
Shut up!
Hold on.
Exactly.
Issue 2.
I... Huh?
Anyway...
it's you!
Y'know...
You guys!
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Seriously?
I'm sorry.
Sorry. No.
Of course.
Togaito...
A locker?!
So listen.
Of course!
Come here.
It's this.
Next time:
This is it.
Yeah, sure.
You coming?
Well, um...
Not at all.
About time.
It's just...
Don't leave!
You're sure?
No, I'm not.
Yeah, kinda.
So you see...
"Chi," is it?
Okay, I give.
I'm so close!
Because you...
Hey, nice hat.
Pretty please?
Great. Thanks.
Yeah? You what?
but my uncle...
And I survived.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Where are they?
Okay, now what?
Well, let's go!
And you are...?
Okay, let's go.
Hold on, Oreki!
He was so smart!
I don't want to.
What's the rush?
Come on, Hotaro.
Okay, time's up.
Yep, it sure is.
I said no, okay?
I... I didn't...
All right, fine.
Hey, first-year.
Well, let's see.
The anthologies.
Well... I dunno.
I'm not, really.
Cigarette smoke.
I started to cry.
"Hey, Little Bro.
Handicrafts Club.
Oh... Uh... Yeah.
There's no point.
The whole school?
Just so you know,
Who said you did?
That explains it.
What's that mean?
More importantly,
So, what'd you do?
but I was bawling.
No, that's not it.
No. Air freshener.
All right, I give.
It's Hotaro Oreki.
What's the matter?
Well, it's just...
I'm not sure what,
I didn't know that.
So that's it, then.
Yeah, you're right.
So what now? Oreki?
We have an opening.
To conserve energy.
It was there, okay?
What issue is that?
Bad news, you guys.
I just want answers.
You won't have to...
What does that mean?
Yep. There they are.
He couldn't risk it.
What... lock... er?!
You think I'm wrong?
Okay. The truth is...
Really? Are you sure?
I don't get "pumped."
Oh well, that's that.
You don't understand!
Just get out of here!
Do you understand me?
I didn't do anything!
So tell me something.
Yeah, that was weird.
You really are weird.
It's what they had...
Why can't I remember?
Hey, sorry about that.
Can you keep a secret?
Wait! Slow down a sec.
To get rid of a smell?
Look! I'm a sunflower!
Here goes! I need help!
I guess I was in shock.
You can do this, Oreki!
She's gotta be kidding.
Midterm tests are over.
It shouldn't be locked.
So what brings ya here?
It's been five minutes.
We should get back now.
It all makes sense now.
That's not all, though.
Take exams, for example.
Greetings from Istanbul!
Admit it. You're pumped.
I can't let that happen.
I thought he was missing.
A chemical locker, huh...
It isn't in here, though.
What on Earth did you do?
I have a favor to ask you!
Maybe you haven't noticed,
Have any more members yet?
And more than once, maybe.
I guess I locked the door.
Then don't just walk away!
Some cardboard boxes, huh?
Why are they so prominent?
Why take such precautions?
What? Oh, the anthologies.
What was special about it?
When I was in kindergarten,
And I've tried to get them.
Huh... I guess it's locked.
What's that smell? Cologne?
Anyway... What do you need?
It's the only clue we have.
Don't you get it? I'm busy!
Isn't that what people say?
"This has been a lot of fun,
So... What happened to them?
I already asked the adviser.
Just trying to be efficient.
Hope you find 'em somewhere.
Where are the other members?
The door should be unlocked.
What is it? Something wrong?
Just look into it some more.
Is that what you want to do?
The Manninbashi home, was it?
You're cool with that, right?
Then there's the room itself.
Inside the locker, obviously.
That's what started all this.
I wanted to ask you something.
I'm sorry, have we met before?
Anyway, sorry I couldn't help.
Go ahead and take a look then.
Sorry. I guess you were right.
How'd you know they'd be here?
Seems like a reasonable guess.
Hey. I'm not messing with you.
Details blur, facts fade away,
I still have so many questions.
This is a big deal to Chitanda.
That's why I'm in such a hurry!
Excuse me! Is anybody in there?
Oh, they're takin' the day off.
What is this guy babbling about?
So let's start at the beginning.
I saw it back when I was little.
Something happened 45 years ago.
The sacrifices that were made...
And he's been missing ever since.
but I'm kind of a private person.
You've got some good timing, Sis.
We just find the chemical locker.
Perhaps they should be forgotten.
Could I get another cup of coffee?
Well... I guess I can manage that.
Then, when I was in middle school,
I'll be sure to tell you about it.
I'm willing to listen to that too.
You have to look in the club room.
So... What can I do for you today?
he panicked and flipped out on us.
The struggles that were endured...
And... Perhaps it is for the best.
Yeah, I'm not really following you.
I asked around in the faculty room,
You think about things differently.
But I will keep your story in mind.
Wanna join the Wall Newspaper Club?
That's cool. And you're a Chitanda.
We're about to hit our 500th issue.
October 13th, 1968. Yoko Koriyama."
So you're just gonna give up, then?
I still don't get why you picked me.
If I find them, that's what I'll do.
We're still missing the first issue!
Why didn't he react when I was upset?
I don't talk about my past very much.
I'll take whatever help you can give!
Thank you! I mean it; thanks so much!
There's also a good amount of tedium.
I already told you, they aren't here.
We need a couple minutes, that's all.
Can't you at least give us that much?
Classic Lit Club member Ibara Mayaka.
And since when are you so tech-savvy?
Check out the ones from 40 years ago.
and asking him about what was inside.
Here, take a look at it for yourself.
Even his smile... All are fading now.
Bit by bit, the truth will be eroded.
I still don't know all of it, though.
That's when I became interested in it.
And for the first time I can remember,
And that secret club recruitment note!
Are you planning to make an anthology?
I'm not seeing what we're looking for.
Why are we waiting out here like this?
so he could start airing out the room?
Huh... So this is what they look like.
"Bit by bit, the truth will be eroded.
he was reluctant to answer my question.
Even if you aren't quite as personable.
Can't we just take a quick look around?
There's no way it's just a coincidence.
It must be what my uncle told me about.
How long till the truth's lost forever?
You're really giving me too much credit.
Well, that's one way to ask for a favor.
Before I say goodbye. For the last time.
What trouble did you get into this time?
"I'm dying to know how the club's going.
It was located in the biology prep room.
So... President of the Classic Lit Club.
Don't you think he's acting kinda weird?
But don't make too much of a mess, okay?
Like with the lock. And the library book.
We could really use a few reinforcements.
I don't think I ever did catch your name.
I see something of him when I look at you.
Chitanda. Take a look at the letter again.
Wow. You're unusually well prepared today.
Too bad. I guess we'll be on our way then.
Of course, if Chitanda didn't have a cold,
I remember taking this volume to my uncle,
After all, it was in no way a heroic tale.
The Sekitani they talk about was my uncle.
That other stuff was just luck, that's all.
There's an unused chemical locker in there.
And the back-number anthologies are inside.
Take care of yourself. Your sister, Tomoe."
It's not just a clubroom, it's a classroom.
But with just the right amount of pressure.
Oh, just a little intimidation, that's all.
It has been a year now since Sekitani left.
I'm sorry. I'm telling this story all wrong.
What made my uncle so hesitant to answer me?
The club is actually the reason I'm writing.
Oh, hey, where's Fukube? I haven't seen him.
I saw you at the Manninbashi home last year.
Yes! Thank you for all you do for my father.
This situation has to be handled delicately.
If you tell me not to say anything, I won't.
Where did the anthologies end up being, huh?
Well... I threw a huge tantrum, to be honest.
I don't care if it's just luck; I'll take it!
It's not like you have anything better to do.
Of course, high school isn't all about drama.
I kind of have a knack for remembering names.
You've obviously heard of the Togaito family.
Until the tale is just another dusty classic.
I mean, look at what it says at the end here.
I guess I'm just not used to talking about it.
Obviously, that includes the Classic Lit Club.
How do we find out where it was two years ago?
You're in class 3-E, right? Togaito, isn't it?
For what it's worth, I'm sorry about all this.
Until the tale is just another dusty classic."
And I want you to help me remember what it was.
But when he told me what I wanted to know, I...
She's spent years obsessing over this question.
It's gonna take forever to sort through it all.
"The Classic Lit Club's Glorious Days of Yore."
I was very fond of him when I was a little girl.
He didn't do anything to comfort or reassure me.
We've become estranged from the Sekitani family,
I want to know the truth about our conversation.
Yeah, you're right, I don't remember seeing one.
It's all right, Chi. Let's just calm down a sec.
I'm just brainstorming ideas for the June issue.
If you recall, it was pointed toward the window,
More precisely, it's called mimeograph printing.
And that makes me think I can trust you, somehow.
Or, more accurately, from the Japanese consulate.
My sister graduated from Kami High two years ago.
They've probably changed the clubroom since then.
That kind of excitement requires too much energy.
Are the anthologies in there? Have you seen them?
The window was wide open and the fan was running.
blowing around the papers that were on the table.
Well then the mystery's just about solved, right?
Here you go. Take a look for yourself if you want.
I didn't realize how much stuff there was in here.
I'm probably the most ordinary guy at this school.
but it involved my uncle and the Classic Lit Club.
So you just find issue one, and there you have it.
No matter what I do, I can't remember what he said!
You are going to keep up the tradition, aren't you?
Anyway, once I reach Pristina I'll give you a call.
I just infer stuff from what I observe, that's all.
I learned that my uncle was in the Classic Lit Club.
Strength in numbers might be your best bet, ya know.
The information we've gathered points straight here.
There are non-members in there all the time, y'know.
That's because they were printed on a Ditto machine.
Besides, looking into it shouldn't be too difficult.
Not if I want all of this settled before his funeral.
it's possible to have them declared legally deceased.
This used to be the Classic Lit Club room, didn't it?
Yep. Our intel says that's where the anthologies are.
It's like he wanted to air out the room or something.
the passage of time polishes the story's rough edges.
It seemed to me that there was nothing he didn't know.
If anyone can help me find the answers I'm looking for,
and we're pretty sure they're in the Biology Prep room.
I think it was, actually, back when I was a first-year.
And I did convince him to answer my question eventually.
I still don't get why you're asking me for help, though.
I know I'm asking a lot of you, and maybe it's not fair.
You answer all my questions, just like my uncle used to.
I think I'll go and ask the club adviser to help us out.
There are some truths that are better left undiscovered.
and I haven't been able to get in touch with them at all.
Sorry to bug you, but we're pretty sure they're in there.
but if you happen to find the anthologies after we leave,
I started wondering about that strange conversation again.
Infrared sensors? What in the world are you talking about?
While you were out doing arts and crafts, we were working.
I don't know if it was because
I was scared or sad or what,
"Once again, the time for the
cultural festival is upon us.
What did my uncle say to me
that day that upset me so much?
But... It says there it might
be best if it were forgotten.
So that's the "personal matter"
you're always talking about?
I really don't think I'll have
anywhere near that much time.
and I know I'll look back in
10 years and be glad I did it."
And if I come across anything
that might give you some clues,
During the testing period, all
club activities are suspended.
All it said was they're in a
chemical locker in the clubroom.
We'll put everything back right
where we found it, I promise.
We don't care about anything
else that might be in this room.
Who knows, maybe something bad
will happen if I keep digging.
This story... isn't the kind
of thing I can tell just anybody.
I heard that they also intend
to hold a small funeral service.
Sorry. I didn't realize this
was the Wall Newspaper Club room.
I don't like the idea of letting
non-club members poke around.
Now that you mention it, we
did take some cardboard boxes out.
Like I told you, I don't want
you making a mess of this place.
Sorry we're inconveniencing
you, but this is really important!
I guess they're best known for
their involvement in education.
I goofed up a bit and haven't
quite made it into the city yet."
Right now, we've got some stuff
to take care of in the library,
But why'd he care so much about
ventilating the room like that?
And if you find out anything
new that you want me to know about,
You wouldn't happen to be one
of the Kanda Chitandas, would you?
The chemical locker had to be
hidden under that makeshift table.
What exactly happened to him at
this school all those years ago?
maybe you could leave them in
the Earth Science prep room for us?
Knowing that the Togaito family
is prominent in academic circles,
This is not really the kinda
thing that I want responsibility for.
And in that year, he has gone
from being a hero to being a legend.
You see? Whatever event they're
referencing happened 45 years ago.
I know it's asking a lot, but
will you please at least hear me out?
Keys to the clubrooms aren't given
out while midterms are underway,
I'll tell you right now, the old
anthologies aren't in the library.
If they aren't here, we're going
to have to search the whole school!
This mentions struggles and
sacrifices, like something big happened.
So when I started at Kami High, I
signed up for the Classic Lit Club.
There's gotta be some other people
who can help you with this, right?
If you're good with those parameters,
then I guess I'll help you out.
And let's not forget the fact that
the place reeked of air freshener.
See, he told me something once...
Something that was really important.
My name's Eru Chitanda, and I'm
the president of the Classic Lit Club.
My guess is that Togaito kept his
cigarettes and lighter in there too.
So, when I suggested we come back
and search the room with an adviser,
There's no telling how much learning
the answer to it might affect her.
And she's asking someone like me to
take on a responsibility like that?
so even if we wanted to meet up
like usual, that wouldn't be an option.
So, the favor I wanted to ask you
has to do with my uncle, Jun Sekitani.
I figured it would be my last chance
to get to the bottom of everything.
We're looking for the old anthologies
the Classic Lit Club put together,
why would he lock himself in and
place infrared sensors out in the hall?
He said something about getting a
head start on the summer fashion scene.
Our club's been writing the Kami
High Monthly Newsletter for a long time.
You didn't notice the small, strange
boxes on either side of the hallway?
Their family holds a lot of important
positions in the educational system.
Of course, I had no way of knowing
that the club was about to be shut down.
It's every student's favorite time of
year here at Kamiyama High: Midterms.
It's a personal matter and not really
something I would normally talk about,
The Classic Lit Club enters an anthology
each year for the cultural festival.
Copy machines didn't become commonplace
until a lot later, so they wouldn't...
The first thing you should know is that
my uncle went to India seven years ago.
Afterwards, I couldn't remember what my
uncle had said, only my reaction to it.
but there weren't any teachers who
remembered a Jun Sekitani from 45 years ago.
You have this way of reaching conclusions
that would have never occurred to me.
This is Issue 2, and it talks about
stuff that happened the year before, right?
One day I asked my uncle about something
having to do with the Classic Lit Club.
Ask a bunch of your friends to help,
and I'm sure you'll get it done in no time.
But we don't really do anything anyway,
so there's honestly not much difference.
but I've given it a lot of thought and
decided that you might be able to help me.
she would've noticed the smell immediately
and things would've been a lot easier.
So I wanna be totally clear that I'm not
agreeing to see this all the way through.
we're pretty sure what we're looking for
is inside some kind of a chemical locker.
Then there was that device with the
antenna on it that was obviously the receiver.
The sound must've startled my mom because
she came rushing in to see if I was okay,
I realize I probably shouldn't be dragging
you into my own personal drama like this.
He must've set it up so that anyone who
passed by the sensors would trigger an alarm.
I especially liked it because the name
reminded me of the vinegar kelp we ate at home.
You've got three whole years of high school
to spend looking for an answer, don't you?
When this became your clubroom, did you
move anything out to make space for your stuff?
The question is, why would he need an alarm
that would tell him when someone was coming
But if someone's been missing for seven
years and no one knows if they're alive or dead,
Declaring him dead would put the matter to
rest and give my uncle's family some closure.
If so, I'm sure you'll want to look at some
examples to know what you're supposed to do.
Unlike most other adults, he would answer all
my questions no matter how silly they seemed.
can you imagine the kind of trouble he would
be in if he was caught doing something illegal?
I don't want a bunch of underclassmen ransacking
my club room! Is that so hard to understand?
When Togaito came to meet us, he stepped out and
closed the door behind him instead of letting us in.
Now... What smell could he be trying to get rid of
that would make him go to such desperate measures?