No.
Oh!
Hm?
Huh?
I...
Yes?
Huh?
Okay.
Look!
Sure.
Mm-hmm.
Hotaro?
Eureka.
Rescue?
Ogi who?
Weird...
I'm not.
Oreki...
For real?
AGM, huh?
Gotta go.
Chitanda!
Oh, well.
Lightning!
Hey, what?
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry.
Next time:
Hey, Oreki!
Yes, ma'am.
Sure thing.
Hey, Oreki.
Here we go.
Okay, then.
Sure. What?
A formation.
Basically...
A helicopter?
Hotaro, wait.
You're wrong!
Knock it off!
It's nothing.
It's strange.
Let me see...
Then again...
That's better.
Wait a minute!
Ugh, whatever.
But not today.
I just mean...
I owe her one.
No. Who's that?
That's so rude.
Try "stranded."
No, I'm serious!
That's so weird.
Completely sure.
Now I'm curious!
had this to say:
Excuse me, Miss.
They're so cute!
And with that...
Oh, okay. See ya.
That sounds good.
Whoa. It's heavy.
A rescue mission.
Yeah, I remember.
That reminds me...
Fine, out with it.
That sounds awful.
Oreki, you made it!
Hi, may I help you?
I'll see you later.
Did I just dream it?
You guys wanna come?
How should I put it?
But this one didn't.
You're very welcome.
That is pretty weird.
You're what? But why?
Mr. Ogi wasn't eager.
...this was my quest.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Struck by lightning...
May, three years back.
People died, you know?
Really? That's amazing!
It was three years ago,
Nope. Not that, either.
I've heard that theory.
Something like it, yes.
But... why would he be?
Then what did it carry?
Well, I gotta be going.
night will have fallen.
We'd all stop and watch.
If my theory is correct.
Was that hard to follow?
Oh! Sorry, you're right.
She can't not have known.
Hey, speaking of Mr. Ogi,
And three times, to boot.
Why don't you ride ahead?
No way; that's not right.
So what did you find out?
Are you sure that was Ogi?
It was just that one time,
Hmph! This story's insane!
He was struck three times!
I just have to know, okay?
Thanks for waiting for me!
Okay. Are you ready to go?
I've turned up 12 results.
Sure, we're happy to wait.
The cover is so beautiful!
You're right, it's unusual,
I'll wrap it up in no time.
I'll look for you; hold on.
Even while he was teaching,
Oh. You have a point there.
Wasn't Ogi into helicopters?
Don't start making stuff up.
You're going to investigate?
This is all incredibly rude.
Since we'll be here a while,
Dung beetles... interesting.
Insensitive's a strong word.
That's very... I don't know.
"Does Anyone Have Any Idea?"
Satoshi. Do you remember him?
But this time it was strange.
And what does that stand for?
Well, according to Mr. Ogi...
No, you go on. I'll catch up.
I see. That's what I thought.
The stakes were high for him.
You know. Ogi. From Class 2-B.
I felt like I was going crazy.
I swear, it actually happened.
...he was struck by lightning!
Wow, that's pretty impressive.
Look at all of these cabbages!
The mountaineers in this town?
They didn't make it, it seems.
She's got it completely wrong!
So then I went to the library.
And you were there to help me.
What is she trying to tell me?
We all went to the same school,
No, it's not really a big deal.
I'm just saying he'd freak out.
There's a ton of stuff in here.
By the time Chitanda gets home,
Yeah, I remember that happening.
But like Fuku said a moment ago,
The man is pretty much a legend.
You're just curious, aren't you?
Not quite how I'd describe them.
Too bad for a helicopter to fly.
I can't think of the right word.
I mean, sure, I remember Mr. Ogi.
...on three separate occasions...
They won't have what I need here.
Would you like to narrow it down?
Pardon... If you wouldn't mind...
They look so juicy and delicious!
Yeah, I remember you saying that.
Maybe "mindful" is a better word.
I'm heading to the public library.
There are so many gorgeous colors!
Now, that is what I call a castle.
Thank you very much for your help.
A dance might be taking it too far.
Hmm... It's all coming back, right?
Yes, they do. Some of them, anyway.
He was really disappointed, though.
but I couldn't bring myself to ask.
I'll call you over when it's ready.
I can give you some, if you'd like!
You're right; that is pretty weird.
Why were you so curious about this?
Come on, don't say stuff like that!
I thought everybody knew about that.
Ibara, does any of this ring a bell?
Hold on a second. What's a squadron?
There's gotta be more to this story.
What have you done with our friend?!
Oreki, is there anything the matter?
What is it you'd like to search for?
Sure. Thank you so much for looking.
And this page with all the tomatoes!
What do you think all of this means?
But then it hit me, no pun intended.
They'd pay attention to helicopters.
What do you mean, "careful"? How so?
I'll probably never see Ogi again...
I didn't exactly ask her to help me.
Ibara, let me try to jog your memory.
Um, that happened like, all the time.
Is something like that even possible?
We truly appreciate your help, ma'am.
There! That's the issue from May 9th!
Like up in the mountains. Am I right?
but I swear it happened, nevertheless.
And how could you tell they were JSDF?
I heard this one from Mr. Ogi himself!
It's novel for you to be so intrigued!
Should I search for specific keywords?
Chitanda can tell where this is going.
I think that part is most likely true.
...but I do remember seeing him smile.
Well, I guess you're right about that.
The way I spoke seems insensitive now.
and Ibara and I were in the same class.
I'd like to read more about it, though.
I can't speak to what he was feeling...
They were found by a police helicopter.
Do you mean Takahiro Ogi from Class 2-B?
It was the talk of the school for a bit.
Three times? How could that man be okay?
"The Kamiyama Mountaineering Association
We'd like to see this newspaper article.
That's what motivated me to investigate.
No, this Ogi taught at our middle school.
I'm sure you'll be back to 100% tomorrow.
I can give you a lift there, if you want.
Hey, Maruta, do you have a minute or two?
When Satoshi told us about the lightning,
their growth rate increased exponentially!
We have a few in the school library, also.
Oreki, you should go straight home to bed.
Would it be okay if I asked you something?
I'm kind of hoping my hunch gets disproven.
But he was struck by lightning three times.
Not someone likely to get hit by lightning.
The bodies of two climbers were discovered.
my mind associated it with something awful.
And that's what I have to be mindful about.
I'm not saying it's impossible, but still...
But only ones that pertain to Kamiyama High.
The association's captain, Masakiyo Ogi, 39,
I've always wanted to take a trip to see it.
and the way he tried to cover was weird, too.
Sure, I'll get right on it. See you in a few.
There's an article from May 9th of that year.
Oh! Look, Oreki, I found the book on insects!
a string of many, 3000-meter-class mountains.
So his feelings might not be of much concern.
Mr. Ogi wasn't especially fond of helicopters.
I shouldn't keep Chitanda waiting for too long.
would you like to look around for a little bit?
Your house is huge. Kind of like a castle, huh?
He was an English teacher, kind of an older guy.
then said something about how he loved choppers,
It's an abbreviation of "air-to-ground missile."
Make yourself some tea and pile on the blankets.
And then he just went back to teaching, remember?
Or have you been brainwashed by one Eru Chitanda?
I found some information on Mr. Ogi in the paper!
Miyajima, the island with the Itsukushima shrine.
Do you really think so? Our house isn't that big.
She didn't even bat an eye at my immutable motto.
It's strange, but I just have to know the answer.
That's fascinating, but we're here to do homework.
He stared at this helicopter until it disappeared,
like he was trying to brush it off as no big deal.
So if you guys don't believe me, I don't blame ya!
You don't mean, like, lightning lightning, do you?
Yeah, but who knows if I'll even turn anything up.
I'd like to do a search of the newspaper archives.
Is this thing with Mr. Ogi worth examining further?
If that's all there are, I'd just like to see them.
and he has burn marks all over his entire body, too.
Even so, why didn't I ever notice any visible scars?
We combed the newspaper for several days after that.
I remember hearing that after starting middle school.
If Satoshi was telling the truth, could Ogi be lying?
I figured that even though he was an English teacher,
I really appreciate you helping me out today, though.
When they're stimulated by a strong current like that,
But I didn't know he was really that into helicopters.
So did you have a hunch that this would be the answer?
mountaineering could've still been his favorite hobby.
Kamiyama sits in the shadow of the Kamikakiuchi range,
If it cleared up, the helicopter would be able to fly,
Yeah, but that's not exactly what I was trying to say.
Oreki, you do work hard all the time for other people.
Satoshi couldn't come because he had too much homework.
Because something has the power to pique your curiosity!
It just doesn't really seem like something you would do.
You've stepped in to help me a lot since I've known you.
He told us he was knocked unconscious one of those times,
He even prefaced by saying it was unbelievable, but true.
It seems like one of those "stranger than fiction" cases.
Oh, is this month's issue a special on Taira no Kiyomori?
Because that particular helicopter had a special purpose.
I wanted to find out whether I was right about it or not.
When we played classical music for our shiitake mushrooms,
Now that you've told me the story, it does sound familiar.
If I hadn't heard it firsthand, I wouldn't have bought it.
I wonder where she's getting her idea of a "normal house."
And are you positive Ogi was
around when all that happened?
I've suddenly remembered another
incredible story about him.
It looks like Chitanda's learned
to play along with Satoshi.
Satoshi. Don't they keep old
newspapers in the city library?
If I didn't know any better,
I would say you were motivated.
Although, apparently the
lightning didn't strike him dead on.
In spite of that, Ogi claims
to have been struck three times.
all he could think about was
the weather up in the mountains.
Even if they just carried aerial
photographers over the range.
Imagine what he felt. He must
have been going through so much.
That sense of not taking how
the other guy feels into account.
But she's the one who offered
to tag along in the first place.
I decided to come to the library
and put my theory to the test.
But that still doesn't mean he
walked away completely unscathed.
Yes, but we can ask at the
information desk on the second floor.
He was desperate to know if the
copter was going to fly that day.
If you happen to come across the
news archives before I get there,
"Mountain trail beautification
efforts in the Kamikakiuchi Range."
Hmm... It's all coming back to
me. Ogi did go crazy for helicopters.
We haven't historically experienced
much lightning here in Kamiyama.
Is it that hard to believe I would
take some spontaneous initiative?
Why did he only look up at the
helicopter on that day and no others?
but I think I would remember if
Ogi had done something similar again.
I believe it's written out as,
"small tree that is correct and pure."
It seems like mountaineering is
one of Mr. Ogi's secret hobbies, huh?
Was this the only mention of him
you found in the newspaper archives?
I would say it's only a little bit
bigger than a normal house, right?
Although... He was really just
your typical Kamiyama English teacher.
and the chances of the stranded
mountaineers' survival would improve.
So, what, am I only allowed to
investigate when you guys are curious?
Well, Oreki, is there anything
around here that you'd like to look at?
Ogi was worried the police wouldn't
be able to send it out on the 9th.
Mr. Ogi was especially eager to see
that lone helicopter doing its job.
I mean, after all, my motto is, "If
I don't have to, I'm not going to."
With all that happened, I shouldn't
talk about it as casually as I did.
I'm dying to know what quest could
have that kind of influence over you!
So I want to know what made you
investigate for your own sake this time.
If it turned out to be true, then I
should be more careful about things.
The article says that on May the
8th, the weather conditions were severe.
Satoshi isn't the type to lie to his
friends for the sake of a good story.
will you go ahead and start looking
through them for the name Masakiyo Ogi?
Even so, I don't remember Ogi having a
particularly strong reaction to those.
Actually, I'm grateful to have the
opportunity to see this other side of you.
Ogi never freaked out about helicopters
after that one flew over during class.
If she can't find the words for it,
then I'm certainly not going to press her.
How could it have made such an impression
on me, yet they don't even recall it?
I'm interested in local happenings from
April and May of about three years ago.
It might take about a half-hour for me
to track down the article for you, okay?
We're interested in reading a particular
newspaper article from a few years ago.
Eleven volunteers took part, primarily
picking up litter and removing overgrowth.
Ibara would have been a lot of help since
she knows the ins and outs of libraries,
That's why, when he heard the sound, he
ran over to the window to see what it was.
But when the squadrons of JSDF helicopters
would fly over, it was an awesome sight.
I even recall wondering if all the middle
school teachers were as weird as Mr. Ogi.
That reminds me, Oreki, we still have a
ton of shiitake mushrooms from the harvest!
It's contained in this compilation of
articles, so you can find what you need here.
It was in English class, 'cause I remember
looking up AGM in the English dictionary.
Because I don't know of any other groups
of helicopters that fly around in squadrons.
Are you the energy conservationist Hotaro
Oreki? Have you been possessed by an alien?
But he did live to tell the tale, so there
is that one consolation, at the very least.
But since it was just a matter of flipping
through old newspapers, it was no big deal.
I'd think if Ogi was into choppers and a
squadron flew over, he'd get up and do a dance.
When Ogi stopped class and voiced his love
for helicopters, it must have been on this day.
However, I've got to say, you're usually
complacent when it comes to working for yourself.
Yeah, and if you expose them to electricity,
like artificial light, they'll get even bigger.
What if he frequently visited a place where
lightning struck a lot more than it does in town?
Just saying that an English teacher stops class
to watch a helicopter doesn't make much sense.
Now think... Do you happen to recall that day
when a helicopter flew over Kaburaya Middle School?
If all of the research required had been a major
undertaking, it would've been a different story.
began sponsoring beautification efforts on the
Abumidake mountain trail on the 26th of this month.
...in such ranges where the peaks are around
3,000 meters, the air currents from below get blocked.
'The current climbing boom could bring with it
climbers who might not be familiar with trail etiquette.
But when you frame it as a mountaineer dropping
everything to watch one, then that's a different story.
they feel threatened, and the fungal filaments
respond by growing bigger to ensure reproductive success.
From what my sister has told me, having been up
into the Kamikakiuchi mountains herself several times...
Mr. Ogi stopped teaching in the middle of class and
ran over to the window to look at something in the sky.
The feature says that Taira no Kiyomori was actually
the child of someone in the Shirakawa palace, I think.
This can cause the weather to vary greatly from the
near to far sides, like two completely different climates.
I think it's important for them to know that a breach of
manners in this environment could cost them their lives.'"