I bet if I picked up a microphone and said,
"Today, the weather will be pleasant,"
anyone from Japan who heard me would just think,
"Oh, Oreki must be testing that microphone."
Ten seconds left.
But people from other countries
would think I was giving a forecast.
They'd assume I just wanted
them to know it would be clear.
Okay, time's up. Pass your papers to the front.
Both assumptions could be considered reasonable.
Both parties have a fifty-fifty shot at being right.
It all depends on luck.
What's the world coming to, man?
I've been wondering...
Your uncle Jun.
Did everything go all right with his funeral?
It turned out very well. Thank you.
Oh, good.
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just...
Oreki...
Could you do me a favor?
Do you think that you could
light some incense for my uncle?
You want me to?
Yes, please.
I am planning to make a trip out to his
gravesite in the next few of days or so.
And, well...
I hoped you'd... come with me.
Yeah, sure.
I'll go.
Oh, great!
I'll be in touch with you about the details soon.
Cool.
I just have to tell you, Oreki,
you have a gift when it comes to mysteries,
and I'm grateful that you solved the one about my uncle.
I think you're amazing.
You know, I appreciate the sentiment,
but I've always just gotten lucky.
I wish you wouldn't treat me
like I'm a big deal or whatever.
You sure are humble. That's impressive.
Aw, man...
She totally missed the point.
Chitanda, I heard something once
upon a time that struck me as profound.
What is that?
"You can put poultice and plausible reason on anything."
Oreki, the saying goes,
"You can put plaster and plausible reason on anything."
Uh... That's what it says?
I just mean you can find reasons
to support anything you want.
If you say so.
Then the reason you've solved all
these cases is only pure, dumb luck,
and it has nothing to do with your intelligence.
And your talent isn't a factor either, okay?
However, you've been able to capitalize on the luck
you've had, and follow through to the correct conclusions.
Now isn't that, in and of
itself, a particular kind of talent?
Are you trying to say I'm a master of reason?
Am I wrong?
Yeah, you are.
I couldn't tell you how I made those deductions.
Honestly, that's the real mystery here.
If I had to guess,
what I would say...
...is that you have never really
taken a good, honest look at yourself.
She's not wrong there.
In that case, Chitanda,
I want you to come up with a situation.
I'll prove to you that I can invent
a good reason for it, whatever it is.
This is a dream come true!
This is the perfect opportunity to show
her that she can't actually rely on me.
All right, then.
What should I pick for you?
Anyone who was shopping at Kobundo
near the train station on October 31st,
please report to Shibazaki in
the faculty room immediately.
What is that all about?
No clue.
Let's make that the situation!
Please deduce why that announcement was made just now!
So what's the story behind it?
Okay, fine.
Challenge accepted.
Right. Here ya go.
Your power of recollection is as intimidating as ever.
That's no compliment.
Let's see...
"Anyone who was shopping at Kobundo
near the train station on October 31st,
please report to Shibazaki in
the faculty room immediately."
First thing we should do is a word check.
Do you know what this "Kobundo" is?
Yes. It's a little stationery
store across from the train station.
It's very quaint, and it's run by a sweet elderly couple.
I've only been there once, though.
What kind of stationery?
Oh, the usual.
North Elementary is nearby, so I think
they might specialize in the kinds of things
grade-schoolers would use.
So it's not the kind of place where
high-schoolers would go out of their way to shop?
I suppose you could say that.
Is Shibazaki on the faculty here?
Oreki, Mr. Shibazaki is the vice principal.
For all your deductive prowess, you're not
good with remembering people's names, huh?
Leave me alone.
"If I don't have to, I'm not going to.
If I have to, I'll do it as quickly as possible."
That was my unshakeable creed.
But the stakes of this contest are high.
I'm going to have to turn up
the heat a little on this one.
First off...
Yes?
I've deduced why Shibazaki would
be calling people in to see him.
Yes. I have a pretty good idea of that myself.
Just to make things clearer, let's refer
to the student who's been called out as "X."
Now we're getting into the swing of things.
Why don't you have a seat?
Okay.
At this point, with the information we have, there's no
way to know whether X is a single kid or multiple people.
Could be anything.
A teaching moment.
He could be trying to teach X a
lesson about something that happened.
In other words, he could be calling X
to the faculty room to chew them out.
What makes you so certain about that?
Because when students are called down to the
faculty room, it's very rarely for something good.
That's what you call inductive reasoning.
Oreki, are you taking this seriously?
I haven't been this serious about
something since I started at Kami High.
I'd go so far as to say I haven't
been this serious my whole life.
Besides, if he was summoning X to
the faculty room to offer praise,
he wouldn't put it in such vague terms.
he would just say that's what was going on.
And he would have called the person out by name.
With an announcement like that, anyone
involved would be too anxious to answer it.
You're right, that's a good point.
Furthermore, that sounded like an urgent page.
You mean 'cause he said, "immediately"?
No, most pages use that word.
It's not that.
This announcement deviated from the standard
pattern, so we can deduce that they made it hastily.
Standard pattern? How so?
Let's say you wanted to make an announcement
addressing me, asking me to come to Class 1-A.
What would you say?
Well, let me see...
Something like this:
"Attention, students:
Would Hotaro Oreki of class 1-B please
report to Eru Chitanda in the 1-A classroom."
Is that really all?
Try to think of other
announcements you've heard this year.
If it were me, I'd say:
"Attention: would Eru Chitanda of Class 1-A
please report to Hotaro Oreki in Class 1-B at once.
I repeat.
Would Eru Chitanda of Class 1-A
please report to Hotaro Oreki
in the 1-B classroom at once."
It's not like a regular announcement.
Usually summons like that are repeated somehow.
But for whatever reason, he
only made this announcement once.
I think it's safe to conclude he was in a rush.
It's not just any run-of-the-mill rush, either.
It's not?
I know that because of when we heard it.
He made the announcement after school.
Hmm... I don't know.
That seems pretty insignificant, if you ask me.
Oh, yeah?
Then I won't say why I think that.
Oreki, come on!
It's just a bit odd.
Why make that announcement after school?
Why not make it earlier in the day?
Sure, Kamiyama may have a ton of
after-school clubs and activities,
but there are still plenty of
students here who leave right away.
That makes me think he made the announcement after school
because the event that caused the
announcement happened after school, too.
And it was urgent enough that he couldn't
risk waiting to summon X until tomorrow.
So that means Shibazaki followed his impulse and
took the gamble that X hadn't gone home from school yet.
I gotta say...
This whole thing feels incredibly shady to me.
Yeah, me, too.
And the term "shady," how did
it come to mean what it does?
Dunno.
Next deduction...
Whatever Shibazaki wants to speak to X about,
that subject can't be discussed out in the open.
Whether that's just for now or
forever, we have no way of knowing.
Do you figure that because Shibazaki
didn't give a reason for making the page?
That's a factor,
but there's an even clearer reason I think so.
It's not clear to me.
Shibazaki is the vice-principal, right?
The guidance counselor is usually
the one who comes down on students.
That's right.
Morishita is always the one to call students in.
Where is the guidance counselor's office?
It's on the second floor of the main building.
But Shibazaki summoned X to the faculty
room, and not the guidance counselor's office.
To me, that means the circumstances were serious.
And that all information about this incident
was to be kept between the administration only.
Or so it could be argued.
Listen... Oreki...
What is it?
Judging by what you've deduced
about this situation so far,
I can't escape the feeling that X was
involved in doing something really bad.
Well, that's what all the signs point to.
So then...
Student X...
...committed some kind of crime.
This is only a game between Chitanda and me.
My explanation doesn't have to match up with the truth.
I mean, the whole point of this was to
prove that my assessments are only right
when I have a good deal of luck on my side.
So, then... What crime could X have committed?
Before we get to that,
if we assume that my deductions are accurate,
we have to note that the school
doesn't have a police officer,
so it's likely that law enforcement has been
summoned here to talk to X about what went down.
If a crime was committed, it
must have happened on October 31st.
And yet the announcement came a few
minutes ago, and seemed really hurried.
It's conceivable that the page followed
immediately after some request from law enforcement.
But that could have been done
relatively easily over the phone.
That may be true,
but if worse came to worse, and
it was decided that X was guilty,
the police might have to take X into custody.
They could have come to the school
just in case that became necessary.
Custody?
Do you mean if X is found guilty
that they would face criminal charges?
Well, it's possible.
Hey. It's a game, remember?
Oh. Right. I keep forgetting.
If X weren't the culprit,
Shibazaki would have waited to make the
announcement, and he wouldn't have sounded so rushed.
That makes sense.
Now as far as what crime we may be
dealing with here, do you have any ideas?
It must have to do with the store somehow.
Well, let's see... Uh...
Shoplifting is the obvious choice.
Beyond that,
it's possible that someone had committed crimes
at other locations, but police received a testimony
that someone of that suspect's description
had been seen shopping at Kobundo,
but if that's the case,
the crime could have been any number of heinous acts.
It could have been anything!
That's a detailed answer for having been put on the spot.
Considering the announcement, I doubt
anyone gave a physical description.
Why's that?
If the police had a description of
someone who had committed a crime,
they would probably share it with Shibazaki.
He would have been able to think of at
least one name, and wouldn't just have said,
"anyone who was shopping at Kobundo" in the announcement.
That's a good point.
The incident occurred at Kobundo,
and all we know for sure was that X
was shopping there on October 31st.
Was the purpose of the announcement
to make X turn themselves in?
If that's the case, it's kind of a weird way to do it.
I speculate...
...that law enforcement doesn't know very much about X,
but they assume that the announcement
will lead X to confess their crimes.
Why would that be?
If I had done something wrong, and
that page came over the PA system...
Anyone who was shopping at Kobundo
near the train station on October 31st,
please report to Shibazaki in
the faculty room immediately.
Ten more seconds.
Good.
The police still don't know I'm the one who did it.
If all goes according to plan, I could get away
with it and go on to become a criminal mastermind!
Why would a guilty party ever come forward
just because they heard an announcement like that?
If they had some sense of remorse about the crime?
No, if that were the case, they'd have turned
themselves in already, and wouldn't be at large.
What are you thinking?
Let's forget about the nature of the
crime for a moment, and try another tactic.
Now suppose X felt guilty about what they had done.
Maybe they decided to apologize to the owners of Kobundo.
In writing.
Wait, in writing?
Chitanda.
Do you know the date off the top of your head?
Of course. It's November 1st.
So the crime was committed yesterday,
October 31st, right?
Why didn't Shibazaki say,
"Kobundo next to the train station
yesterday," in his announcement?
Now that you mention it, that is quite unusual.
Why would someone spell out October
31st instead of saying "yesterday"?
One explanation could be that they have
some sort of form or note in front of them
on which all that is written out, and
they are reading the date directly from it.
A form or a note, huh?
Yeah.
Furthermore, why do the police know that X was
involved in a crime, but have no idea what X looks like?
Why would they assume that X would
come forward just because they were paged?
To put it another way, why would
they think X felt remorse for the crime?
It has to be that X sent an apology note to Kobundo.
It probably went something like this:
"I am terribly sorry.
I was shopping in your store on October
31st and committed an unlawful act.
I intend to pay for the damage I caused, so
please accept such and such and my sincere apology."
Kobundo then takes that apology
note directly to the police.
Either the police or other law
enforcement follows up on the letter,
and decides to come to Kami High.
That just happened, mere moments ago.
Then Shibazaki reads the note and is so outraged
that he makes a hasty schoolwide announcement,
summoning the suspect to the faculty room.
Hold on a minute.
Oreki, by your logic, even though
X wanted to apologize to Kobundo
and repay them for the damage, they hoped
by writing the letter that they could settle
without any police involvement, right?
Yeah, that makes sense.
In that case, I don't think X
would have indicated in their letter
that they were a student at Kamiyama High, would they?
So then how would the police
have known to look for them here?
Maybe when police asked the owners of Kobundo
for a physical description of the suspect,
they detailed X's clothes, and police put
together that it was the uniform for Kami High.
That would be one possible explanation.
Interesting.
And if X did anything that made them stand out, it
would make sense for the owners to remember details.
What would make them stand out?
Well, let's see.
We might be able to determine the crime from that.
So, X behaved oddly.
They did something outrageous enough to attract
attention, but that's not necessarily illegal.
Then X committed a crime,
the nature of which is such that, without the
apology letter, no one would have known right away.
X was consumed with regret.
X's crime was serious enough that it
warranted contacting law enforcement immediately.
Whatever X did yesterday...
It wasn't something petty, like shoplifting.
Then, what?
Shopping in a way that stood out.
Shopping that became illegal.
You said that Kobundo is a stationery
store that caters to grade school kids,
so it's not likely that they carry anything of much value.
Shopping... shopping... shopping.
No way.
What is it?
Our friend, X, tried to pay
with a counterfeit 10,000 yen bill.
But... But...
But that can't be true!
It's just way too far-fetched.
I don't think it's realistic!
It defies any sort of logic!
It's a terrible theory! It's completely catastrophic!
Whoa. Hey.
Calm down.
This is just a game, you know?
Right. I'm sorry.
It's not real. Don't take it so seriously.
I know, but still...
It's not possible... It can't be.
Why are you so sure it's impossible?
It's been all over the news that someone
has been trying to pass off 10,000 yen bills.
That's what gave you the idea in the first place:
That X must be someone from our school who
tried to pay with one of them yesterday, right?
Yeah.
But X could not have possibly gotten
ahold of one of those counterfeit bills,
or even if they had, they would have realized
it was fake and handed it over to the police.
What makes you say that?
Bear with me here.
Let's say X did get a counterfeit bill.
Where do you think they could have done that?
From an ATM, I would imagine.
Counterfeit bills that are good enough to slip
past bank tellers into an ATM aren't very common.
And even if by some chance that happened,
the bill would be so good that X wouldn't spot it.
If X was given change, Oh.
That's right.
You can't get 10,000 yen bills as change.
Except for commemorative coins, the
10,000 is the highest note there is here.
I think I see what you're getting at now.
That means there's only one or two other ways in
which X could have acquired a fake bill innocently.
But even if we assume X's parents own their own
business, and had a counterfeit bill given to them
without their knowledge,
if X had gotten it as allowance or something,
X would have had the chance to
tell his or her parents it was a fake.
I think you're right.
And if X had earned it at a part-time job or something,
they would have had a chance to turn it in then, as well.
What if X found it?
That would be too crazy!
Yeah, someone who would find a counterfeit bill
and try to pass it off as real doesn't seem
like the kind to write an apology letter, do they?
X probably noticed at the last minute and
felt guilty as they were trying to pay with it.
Without knowing how X obtained a counterfeit bill, it's
impossible to say whether your deduction is realistic.
A 10,000 yen note.
Chitanda. Would you say that you like money?
I'm not sure.
I suppose it's fair to say I
like it more than I dislike it.
If you dropped 10,000 yen, would you miss it?
Yeah, of course I would.
Well... Unless I knew my money wasn't the genuine article.
If it was your own, real money,
then I bet you would miss it for sure.
The reason X felt guilty, even while committing
the crime, is that it was their own money.
Even if it was a fake.
I submit that X must have gotten that bill
from someone, thinking it was legitimate currency,
and if that wasn't from wages or
allowance, there's only one other possibility.
Someone gave it to them when they repaid a loan.
If X had gotten the bill in that
manner, and discovered it was a fake,
they'd have been really disappointed.
That being the case, it's hard to blame them for
trying to use it at a store run by an old man and woman.
Even if they knew it was immoral to do that.
Even so, they still would have had the opportunity
to turn it in and exchange it for real money!
I don't know.
A fake bill is like the joker in Old Maid.
No one wants to get stuck with it.
You know, the longer I think about
this, the more plausible it sounds to me.
"Hey, X, I have the money that I
borrowed from you a while back."
"Ah, Y, that's great. I appreciate it."
"It was 10,000 yen, right? Here ya go."
"Yes, thank you."
Then, surprise, it's a fake bill.
Maybe Y, who borrowed the money from X,
had seniority over X, complicating things.
So X didn't feel like they could object
when Y paid them back with a counterfeit note.
At this point, I think it's safe
to say that X is just one person.
And since Kobundo is a store that sells
inexpensive stationery for grade school kids,
it would be weird for high schoolers to
come in buying things with 10,000 yen bills.
I think that wraps that up.
Then there's Y.
Y also came across a fake bill.
It could be that Z, someone above Y, gave it to them.
If we lump everyone above Y together
as one collective, then who are they?
A store manager somewhere with no
conscience, or the counterfeiter themselves?
The police may have gotten involved at Kami
in the hope that they could find out from
X specifically where the counterfeit bills
were originating. That's my guess.
And that concludes my deduction.
Hmm...
After I talked for so long, it seems
kind of rude of her not to respond.
Whatever.
Kobundo is over that way, isn't it?
That's amazing.
"Anyone who was shopping at Kobundo
near the train station on October 31st,
please report to Shibazaki in
the faculty room immediately."
A whole story. Wow. Just from that one announcement.
Yeah, that's what we came up with.
Game over, I guess.
Hey, Oreki.
Huh? What is it?
I seem to remember that we started this whole game as a
way to settle an argument we were having about something.
Oh, that rings a bell.
Now what was it, again?
I can't recall.
Oh, Oreki... I have an idea.
Do you want to deduce what it was?
Give me a break.
Whoa...
But that was supposed to be a game.
I thought...
It couldn't possibly be true. Hmm.
Next time:
"Mishap-py New Year."