♪ Opening Song ♪
We need to take cover!
[BERTHOLDT panting]
[BERTHOLDT]
It hurts.
It hurts so badly.
[ARMIN gasping]
[ARMIN]
Bertholdt...
[SASHA]
It hurts...
[gasps]
[SASHA groans]
It hurts so badly.
Wait, are you--?
Whoa. Sasha!
You're in horrible shape.
What happened to you?
[EREN]
You're up!
[ARMIN]
Eren.
Armin. I'm so glad you're back.
[LEVI]
'Bout time.
[ARMIN]
Captain!
What happened?
I saw Bertholdt transform,
but then everything gets
kind of blurry. [gasps]
Did we fight them off?
Is everyone okay?
It sounds like your recent
memory was just about wiped out.
[ARMIN]
Huh?
[LEVI]
Eren. Tell him everything.
Okay. Are you up to speed now?
Yeah.
We won.
But of the Scout Regiment,
there are only nine
soldiers left alive.
The nine of us.
That's what it looks like.
The fighting ended
four hours ago.
We've been searching for
survivors, but... no luck.
So, to be clear, we resealed
Shiganshina's gate,
securing Wall Maria.
Reiner and the
Beast Titan escaped,
along with that quadruped.
You managed to
capture Bertholdt.
And then, with both the
commander and me wounded,
you had to choose which of
us to give the injection to.
And you did.
I transformed into a Titan
and killed Bertholdt.
I ate him.
[ARMIN pants, gags]
[ARMIN coughs]
[JEAN]
Here.
[gasps, pants]
Why though?
Why'd you pick me?
No matter how you look at it,
Commander Erwin's the one
humanity needed the most.
Captain!
Why'd you give me the injection?
Tch. Hey.
I thought I told you to
tell him everything, Jaegar.
There was a short debate.
Your friends here
argued that you were
the one we needed to revive.
And when I disagreed,
they staged a little mutiny.
It's true.
Punish us as you will.
You'll certainly be disciplined
for your insubordination.
But getting punished isn't
the same as making amends.
I know.
Thing is,
I was the one who chose
to revive you in the end.
Or no.
It's more like I chose this to
be the place where Erwin died.
Sorry. I just don't understand.
How could letting Erwin die
be the right thing to do?
What are the Scouts without him?
If he's gone,
then how will we go on?
You're right, Armin.
I believe it should've
been used on Erwin, too.
To be brutally honest--
[HANGE]
Nevermind.
It's a shame we had to
choose in the first place.
It's over now.
Erwin told Levi to use the
syringe as he thought best.
And Levi chose to use it on you.
What's done is done.
Erwin's life and
the power of a Titan
both rest on your shoulders.
No matter what anyone says,
that's the truth.
It's part of who you are now.
Accept it.
Wait... so does this...
...mean that I need to
become Erwin's replacement?
There's no way.
I can't!
Don't misunderstand us.
There's no chance in hell
that you could replace Erwin.
That said,
your self-doubt aside,
you have a strength within you
that no one else can claim.
[ARMIN gasps]
[LEVI]
Don't let any of us regret this.
Not me,
not either one of
our mutineers here,
nor anyone else.
[LEVI] And especially
don't regret it yourself.
Consider that your new mission.
[SASHA grunts]
[gasps]
Shut the hell up.
[ALL gasp]
[HANGE chuckles]
Yup. That's our Sasha.
She's always been one
to speak her mind.
You know,
since Erwin chose me to
succeed him as commander,
I'm more or less in
the same boat as you.
We'll just have to
grin and bear it,
while doing what we can.
I'll try.
[HANGE]
Good.
Now that we know
Armin's all right,
let's check out that cellar.
Eren, Mikasa.
You two can come
guide me and Levi.
The rest of you stay.
Keep an eye out for hostiles
from here on the wall.
--Right!
--Got it.
[HANGE]
Eren, do you still have the key?
I do.
Let's do this.
[GRISHA]
Eren.
Behave while I'm gone
and I'll let you in on what
I've been doing in the cellar.
Agreed?
[CARLA]
Eren!
How many times have I told
you to stay out of there?
I don't get why it's
such a big deal.
Because your father keeps
his work tools down there.
Medicine, too.
It's dangerous for children.
Fine.
[ERWIN]
It's why I ask your intentions.
They could be the key to
turning the tide forever.
You could save us.
Intel suggests that the cellar
of Jaeger's home in Shiganshina
holds a vital secret
regarding our enemy.
We will form an expedition
to find this secret.
With that achieved,
we may finally be able to
break free from the Titans,
and bring an end to
their hundred-year reign.
Well, takes us to your house.
[EREN]
Yeah. Right.
Is this the place?
[EREN]
Hey, Dad!
When'll you show me
what's in the cellar?
Well,
perhaps when you've realized
the most important thing of all.
Luckily for us, the fires burnt
out before they got this far.
This is it.
The stairs to the cellar
are beneath this door.
All right.
[ALL grunting]
That's a relief.
I was worried that it
might've flooded by now.
Let's go.
Do it, Eren.
Right.
[EREN gasps]
You okay?
What's wrong?
Hurry it up.
[EREN gasps]
I can't.
The key--
It doesn't go to this door.
[HANGE]
What?
[MIKASA]
That doesn't make sense.
I'm sure it's the key
that Dr. Jaeger had.
[LEVI]
Step aside. I'll open it.
Wait, what?
[LEVI grunts]
[MIKASA, EREN gasp]
That'll do it.
[HANGE] It almost feels like
a laboratory down here.
[EREN]
My dad was a doctor,
so he was always cooped up
down here mixing medicines.
[HANGE]
That makes sense.
Actually, if we assume that all
of this is labeled accurately,
most of it seems to
be widely available.
And all of the books on
hand relate to medicine.
This looks like a
normal doctor's study.
There isn't a single thing here
that would rouse my suspicion,
as I'm sure your
father intended.
Right.
If you wanna hide something
from the Interior Police,
you wanna be sure not
to give them any leads.
Hey.
Don't just stand
there, get to work.
Erwin's hunches
are rarely wrong.
[EREN, MIKASA]
Right.
[gasps]
Thanks for the drink, Mikasa.
Looks like another all-nighter.
[MIKASA]
Eren.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[MIKASA]
Look. I found a keyhole.
Try it.
[EREN]
That got it.
It's empty?
Look closer.
There's a false bottom.
[EREN gasps]
[HANGE sniffs]
The cloth smells like
peppermint oil and charcoal.
Guess he was using these to
ward off moisture and bugs.
If what we were looking for
exists, then we've found it.
After all this time,
Dad might finally
explain himself.
[NILE]
Then Erwin raised his hand
and asked the
strangest question.
"How can we be sure
there aren't other humans
living far away from the walls?"
His thinking was that since
we'd never been able to
search freely beyond the walls,
we had no way of confirming
that the rest of humanity
had been wiped out
by Titans completely.
[ERWIN] And yet, that's exactly
what our historians would claim.
[NILE]
Hmm?
[ERWIN]
Think.
If our history books
would claim to be unbiased,
the phrasing should be
"it's believed that the
rest of mankind was killed."
If I'm being honest,
I feel like you're just
splitting hairs here.
I'm not!
This was a deliberate
choice they made!
These books--
They're commissioned and issued
by the royal government itself.
Get it?
Their intent is to
make us believe
we're the only humans left.
Maybe they just assumed.
Aren't you reading a
little too far into this?
Back then I made
fun of his theory,
but he may have been right.
If he is, you'll just
have to apologize to him.
[PYXIS sighs]
Look there.
The sun's rising.
If our heroes are going to
return, it should be soon.
[ANKA]
Um! Pardon!
But the Scouts came
back a moment ago!
They did it!
They reclaimed Wall Maria!
[CROWD cheering]
Is this a painting?
Let me look closer.
[HANGE]
No.
This is far too detailed to have
been drawn by a human hand.
[MIKASA]
Uh--hey.
There's writing on the back.
"This is no illustration.
It was made by
gathering the light
reflected off the subject"...
[HANGE, GRISHA]
...and burning it into an image
on special paper.
Looks quite nice, right?
Where I'm from,
there are many amazing
technologies like this.
Mankind isn't gone.
[GRISHA]
Beyond the walls,
countless humans live in
comfortable refinement.
I pray the person who finds this
book will be a fellow patriot.
♪ Closing Song ♪
[GRISHA] Hurry, Fay! If we're
not fast, we'll miss it!
[FAY]
Wait up, Grisha!
[GRISHA'S MOTHER]
Not so fast. Come here.
Don't forget again.
You can't go outside
without your armbands.
And Grisha,
you mustn't go past the
walls for any reason.
--[FAY giggles]
--Hey, wait for me!
[FAY giggling]
Don't worry, Mom, we'll be good.
Yeah, we'll see ya later, okay?
--So where to?
--This way. Come on!
[GRISHA]
When I first considered
how best I should
start my story,
my thoughts turned
to that day at once.
[BOTH laughing]
Hey!
--Grisha?
--Sorry 'bout that!
Watch where you're
going, will you?
And slow down a bit!
[FAY]
Aww, it's leaving.
I love it!
When I'm rich someday,
I wanna ride in an airship that
looks exactly like that one!
[GRISHA]
What are you talking about?
There's no way either
of us'll get rich.
[FAY] I know, but it's
nice to pretend.
I wonder what all we
could see from up there.
[FAY]
There it goes.
--Come on, Fay!
--Hey! Wait!
Where are we going?
My teacher told me something.
He said the airships
land at a place nearby.
Let's go and watch!
Really?
But Mom said we shouldn't leave
the walls no matter what!
It'll be fine! We'll just
be gone for a minute!
--Be right back, sir!
--Hey!
Stop right there!
[GRISHA] The fateful day
that I, just a naive youth,
was made to face the
truth of this world.
[NARRATOR] His story began
when he took his sister's hand
and stepped forward,
while gazing up at the sky.
The hope and hatred in his eyes
show Eren a world far from
his own, but just as cruel.
Next episode: "That Day."