[NARRATOR] Levi and the Scouts
clashed with Kenny's squad,
charging straight into
their defenses.
All to find and rescue
Eren and Historia.
However...
[HANGE groans]
[CAVEN grunts]
[yells]
[HANGE groans]
We'll re-form our defense
at the fallback point!
Time to regroup!
I'm praying right now, Historia.
For God to return and
lead mankind once again!
[CHRISTA]
God my ass!
If it's such an honor
to become him,
then why didn't you
do it yourself?
I'm done with your shit,
and I'm not gonna
let you murder me!
[KENNY laughing]
That's the spirit!
This is gettin' good!
[CHRISTA]
You get the hell out of here.
I'll deal with the rest.
[ROD]
Father.
Uri.
And Frieda.
Just wait.
♪ Opening Song ♪
[LEVI panting]
[LEVI] Might be a way through.
But it's blocked.
Shit. If only we had
some more gunpowder.
[CAVEN] Keep your guns
trained on that entrance.
If we hold them here, we win!
[CAVEN gasps]
--[JEAN] That light.
--Damn it. No.
Eren!
[distant roar]
[EREN, CHRISTA groan]
[KENNY grunts]
[CAVEN]
Everyone, brace yourselves!
Hey guys, this place
is about to collapse.
[ARMIN]
Captain!
It opened up!
Okay, Armin! Moblit!
You two take Hange and
find a way out of here!
Stupid bastard.
What the hell are you doin'?
Just leave me, Historia!
That Titan's from your family!
Let him eat me and
everything'll be all right!
Get out of here!
--Not a chance!
--Why won't you listen?
I might be an enemy
of humanity now,
but I'm still your ally!
I can't be selfless,
and I don't want to be a god.
But... when I see
someone crying,
saying that no one's needs them,
I have to go and show them
that it isn't true!
You're feeling like I felt
for my entire life.
That's why I need you
to be okay!
[EREN gasps]
[CHRISTA]
Uh!
Historia!
--Uh!
--Hey.
Mikasa!
Give me the keys!
Captain. All of you.
Conny, hurry!
Just leave me here. Forget it!
Hurry up and escape!
Stop whining!
Ya half-naked weirdo!
We've got gunmen and a Titan
coming at us, so pipe down!
Feet're loose!
[SASHA] Whoa. It's even bigger
than the Colossal Titan. Crazy.
[gasps]
[MIKASA]
The ceiling. Look out!
Get back!
[KENNY]
Damn it all, Rod!
You really screwed the pooch.
Here I thought you were
the one man alive
that understood Titans,
but you didn't know enough.
You dumbass!
[CAVEN]
Captain Ackermann!
No! Get back!
Damn it. We'll be buried alive!
[EREN] Why? Shouldn't he
be trying to eat me?
Should I transform?
No. My Titan would
only get crushed.
Sorry. I can't.
I've been dead weight
every damn step of the way.
This power never
should've been given to me.
I can't be humanity's hope.
I'm just too weak.
Armor?
[JEAN] C'mon. Stop playin'
the tragic hero.
Of course you're too weak
to accomplish jack by yourself,
but no one expects you to.
Yeah, calm it down.
We've been through a whole lot
worse than this, man.
Not that I really
wanna get used to it.
[CONNY] Still, it's gonna suck
tryin' to fly through that mess.
I'll take Eren.
It's gonna take all
we have to not get hit.
--So hold on for your life.
--Right.
It's useless. You know
we won't make it.
So we should do nothing?
Wanna sit here and hold hands
'til we're crushed?
Or 'til we burn to death?
You know dying here
won't make anything better!
Listen. I really hate that I do
this to you all the time, but...
You've gotta
make a choice here.
I'm with you!
[EREN yelling]
Eren!
[EREN] I'm sorry.
But since it's the end,
this one time, just let me.
Let me believe I can do this!
Whoa. What the--?
Come on! Get under Eren!
[gasps]
[yells]
[SOLDIER 45A]
Caven!
[KENNY gasps]
[roars]
What's going on?
Whoa, look out!
We just need to keep moving!
[ALL groan]
Section Commander! Are you okay?
[HANGE]
Yeah. What happened?
[distant rumbling]
[SOLDIER 45B]
What the hell is that?
If it's that big
from a distance...
That thing must be
at least twice the size
of the Colossal Titan.
It'll break through
the wall in an instant.
What now?
We advance!
[MIKASA]
Eren. [grunts]
Can you hear me?
Wake up!
[EREN gasps]
Eren!
[LEVI]
Not too shabby, Eren.
Even after we cut you from it,
the Titan hasn't disappeared.
This could be a game changer.
I almost forgot.
Listen, before I transformed,
I drank from a bottle
that said "armor."
Gotcha. Guess that's all
you needed to pull it off,
because this time
you did it easily.
You saved all our lives.
You came up with and
built everything we see here
in the blink of an eye.
It's not exactly pretty,
but I can see its potential.
I bet this is how
the walls were made too.
Guess what?
This means we finally
have a real shot
at plugging the hole
in Wall Maria.
[gasps]
[LEVI] We had a hell of
a time getting here.
Took long detours.
Watched friends die.
But as ugly as it's been,
look at the position
we're in now.
[EREN] If we can pull it off,
and retake Wall Maria,
I can finally go to the cellar.
But knowing what my dad did...
[EREN]
Mm.
[SASHA]
Captain!
We've secured an exit, sir!
[CONNY] Hange's fine!
Armin and Moblit, too!
I'm glad to hear it.
Eren!
You okay?
[SASHA] Uh! We're all
safe, thanks to you!
But to be completely honest,
when I saw you run off
into the light,
stumbling like a drunk
and wailing like a baby,
I thought we were screwed!
You looked like an idiot and
my fate was in your hands.
It was awful!
Quit your bawling!
Have some dignity!
That's what I was
thinking anyway.
Relax.
Let's go. We have
a big-ass Titan to catch.
Hey. Here.
[EREN grunts]
[gasps]
[SOLDIER 45C]
Uh! Damn it.
It's too hot.
We can't get close.
[SOLDIER 45B] Commander.
We can't seem to distract it.
It's an Abnormal.
It doesn't care about us.
That's all right. Fall back.
We know what direction
it's going.
That tells us enough
to make a plan.
[SOLDIER 45D] We found
Levi Squad! They're nearby!
They succeeded, sir!
They have Eren and Historia!
[gasps]
--[horse neighs]
--[LEVI] Erwin.
[ERWIN]
Anyone hurt?
[LEVI]
Yeah, Hange took a hit.
Doesn't look like
anything too serious.
You've done excellent work,
all of you.
[LEVI] I've got a whole slew
of things to report, but first--
Anything on that Titan?
[LEVI]
It's Rod Reiss.
[gasps]
Look forward to hearing
your thoughts on this.
Commander.
Time's short. We can't afford
to stand here and chat.
Head back to the wall.
[LEVI] You're gonna let
that thing drag its fat ass
all the way to Sina?
Well, more specifically,
I'm letting it continue
towards Orvud District.
All right. Time to think.
First off, Lord Reiss was after
the Founding Titan's power.
And that power currently
resides within Eren.
Thing is, the Founding
Titan can only be used
at full potential
by someone of royal blood.
But then, when a royal
does obtain
the Founding Titan's power,
they suddenly take on
the First King's ideology,
which means they'll refuse
to do anything about the Titans.
Well, this certainly
is a conundrum.
So the First King thinks
this is true peace, huh?
I'm gonna have to go ahead
and disagree with him there.
You know, we still have
the option to go back.
We just need that Titan
to eat me,
and Reiss will become
a human again.
We could still have
a true Founding Titan.
It's possible.
[MIKASA gasps]
Wait, you don't mean?
--It's worth considering.
--[MIKASA gasps]
Once Reiss turns back into
a human, we could capture him,
and undo the First King's
brainwashing.
Assuming that it can be done,
it may well open a path
to save humanity.
Tell me, Eren.
If that turns out
to be our best bet,
are you really willing to do it?
Yes, I am.
Eren. I can't let you.
Let's not forget
the other option.
[CHRISTA] First off,
the plan you're discussing
is full of flaws.
For one thing,
it might not be possible
to free my father from
the First King's will.
And no matter
how you restrain him,
if he alters everyone's
memories, we're finished.
And consider how much there is
that we still don't know
about the Founding Titan.
This isn't worth the risk.
She's right, you know.
It's not even guaranteed
that Reiss would
turn back to normal
if he did eat Eren.
That's just a hypothesis.
No one's actually
seen it happen before.
[CHRISTA]
Mm.
So far, we've only been led
by destructive pacifists.
And if they'd kept
the Founding Titan's powers,
that's how it would stay.
This is humanity's first chance
to escape from them.
[EREN gasps]
Eren. Your father wasn't evil.
He was trying to save humanity
from the First King.
[CHRISTA] He stole the Founding
Titan from my sister,
and then he murdered
my father's wife and children
because he had no other choice.
[GRISHA]
Mikasa's life. Armin's life.
Everyone's life
hinges on your being able
to control this power!
You mean...
Yeah, that's right.
The Doctor Jaeger I knew
would only have done
something like that
if he felt like he had to.
Agreed. He must've
known of another way.
A way to save humanity
without Reiss blood.
And that must've been
why he left you
the key to the cellar.
What? Your cellar?
Oh, yeah, right.
I'd forgotten all about that.
You mean it's actually
important now?
Apparently, it is.
What matters most to me
is that we have a way
to plug Wall Maria.
The way I see it, that makes
our choice pretty clear.
You know, that's actually
a fairly convincing argument.
For whatever it's worth,
I think we should
stick with Eren too. But listen.
Are you sure
about this, Historia?
That Titan's a major threat.
It's not like we can just
let it wander around
freely inside the walls.
Capturing it isn't an option--
it's way too big.
Which means that...
...our only way forward
is to kill your father.
♪
Eren. I should apologize.
What?
Under the Reiss Chapel.
I really considered turning
into a Titan and killing you.
[MIKASA gasps]
[CHRISTA] And honestly,
it wasn't to save humanity.
I just wanted to believe
my father was right.
Even more than that,
I wanted him to like me.
But it's time for me
and him to part ways now.
--[clanging]
--[horse neighing]
Please have your squad
stand by in the hall now.
They're almost ready
to begin the meeting.
We'll be right there.
[LEVI]
Historia. I forgot to tell you.
There's something
we need you to do.
What's that?
This is an order from Erwin.
Once we finish off this Titan,
seeing as you're the true
successor to the throne,
you'll become queen.
[ALL gasp]
--[ALL gasp]
--[SASHA] Wait. Queen Historia?
You're kidding, right?
The coup d'état was successful,
but the people won't follow
military rule forever.
We need to give them
a heartwarming story.
One where the rightful heir
retakes her crown
from the pretender.
Oh, I see.
Hey. Uh, you heard what
Historia was saying earlier,
didn't you, Captain?
'Cause, well, it sounded
to me like, maybe,
in siding against her dad,
she finally broke off
from that part
of her life, ya know?
It's just like--
Like what? You have something
to say, then say it.
[CONNY]
Um. I--
Hey, Captain?
What Conny's trying
to say, is that Historia
finally broke free
from the Reiss family,
and decided she's
more than just a bloodline.
So for us to force her
into another role,
for that reason... I...
I just don't think it's fair.
--[CHRISTA] It's fine.
--Huh?
If my next duty
is to become a queen,
then that's what I'll do.
But Historia.
I do appreciate your concern,
but whether this is
"forced" on me is really
up to me to decide.
And I've decided.
Captain. Before that,
I have one condition for you.
[LEVI]
And that is?
[CHRISTA]
While my fate is still my own,
I want to put everything
I have on the line.
♪
Once you're queen,
you can punch that smug runt
right in the face.
[SOLDIER 45E]
Sirs.
We have determined
the Reiss Titan's location.
It's southwest,
approaching Orvud.
It's fast. At this rate,
it'll reach the walls
before dawn.
Right, understood.
Commander Erwin.
I'm sure everyone here
would like to hear your plan.
How can we evacuate the people
in such a short time?
That's not part of the plan.
What's that?
The people of Orvud District
will need to stay
exactly where they are.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
But Commander.
♪
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] At Orvud District,
Eren and the others
face off against
Rod Reiss' Titan.
Despite the danger,
Historia is determined
to decide her own fate.
Next episode:
"Ruler of the Walls."