♪ Opening Song ♪
I was born on a small farmstead
in the northern lands
of Wall Rose.
It was owned by
the noble Reiss family.
As far back as I can remember,
I was helping out
around the farm.
But my mother was
always reading books.
She didn't care to work.
And no one cared to make her.
She was a beautiful woman.
Most nights, someone would
come for her in a carriage,
and she'd go off into the city,
wearing fancy clothes.
[HORSE neighs]
[CHRISTA] For me, that was
just life as I knew it.
But when I learned
to read and write,
I started picking up books
to imitate my mother.
And they taught me
just how alone I was.
In all the stories
I read in those books,
parents cared
about their children.
They talked to them,
hugged them, scolded them.
I had never experienced
any of those things.
One day, out of curiosity,
I decided to try
hugging my mother.
I guess I just wanted to see
what kind of face she'd make.
--[CHRISTA] Mommy!
--[ALMA gasps]
--[CHRISTA giggles, screams]
--[ALMA grunts]
[CHRISTA] She ended up
shoving me away from her.
But that was the first time
my mother had acknowledged me.
So it actually made me happy.
If only I wasn't such a coward,
I could've killed it.
[CHRISTA] Those were the first
words my mother ever said to me.
She went to live
somewhere else after that.
I didn't see her
for a long time.
And then, five years ago,
just a few days after
Wall Maria fell...
...I finally met my father.
Historia. My name's Rod Reiss.
I wish that we
could've met sooner.
You see, I'm your father.
[gasps]
[CHRISTA]
That man. He was the lord
of the land I'd grown up on.
The mother I hadn't
seen in years
looked terribly frightened.
Now, listen. You'll be living
with me from this day forth.
[ALMA gasps, screams]
[KENNY] You know
what this is, Lord Reiss.
The fall of Wall Maria's
got you acting a bit reckless.
I suppose you thought you'd get
your pretty little secrets
to safer ground, huh.
--[ALMA sobbing]
--Let Mom go!
No! I'm not that girl's mother!
I've never even met her!
Do whatever you want
with her, but let me go!
Oh? You have anything to
say about that, Lord Reiss?
Maybe it's just a coincidence
the three of you
are out here at the same time.
[ROD sighs]
So be it.
That's correct--these two
have nothing to do with me.
I thought that
might be the case.
[ALMA gasps]
Wait? What are you--?
You were never employed
at this estate.
And nobody here
has ever heard your name.
Sounds to me like
you don't exist.
No, I-- Master, please!
That isn't true,
you have to tell them!
What are they... doing? Mother?
If only you had never
been born, I could--
[CHRISTA] Those were the last
words my mother ever said.
No. Wait.
[CHRISTA] Moments before
I was killed myself,
my father proposed an idea.
That if I were
sent somewhere far away,
to live out a quiet life,
perhaps they could spare me.
Your new name will be...
...Christa Lenz.
I beg for your
forgiveness, child.
Please know that
everything I've done
I did to protect you.
F-Father.
[ROD] Not a day has passed
that I haven't thought of you.
Long have I dreamed of a day
when I could hold you like this.
You are special.
The blood of the king
flows through your veins.
Is that true?
[ROD]
Yes, Historia.
The true royal bloodline is
carried by the Reiss family.
And as its heir, the power
to save all of humanity
now rests in your hands.
Please Historia, come with me.
And I'll show you
where it all began.
[jingling, click]
[clang]
[RALPH] Sannes!
Your face. What happened?
Wait, did you--?
They didn't actually
make you talk, did they?
But we swore a vow
of loyalty to the king--
[SANNES yelling]
I can't stand to hear
another word out of you!
I would've died for you,
and you betrayed me for a bed!
[RALPH groaning]
[SANNES]
To think I trusted you!
Hey. He never told us anything.
He didn't get a chance to--
we never questioned him.
[SANNES gasps]
This is the
conversation you heard.
We forced Ralph here to read
off this script at knifepoint.
It was staged.
[BOTH gasping]
[coughing]
Then... it was me.
I'm the one who betrayed
the king's secret.
You. You're a devil.
Yes, I think you might
be right about that.
But I bet Pastor Nick felt
the exact same way about you.
That's why I felt
sorry for you, Sannes.
Not because your nails
got plucked out,
but because of what
you've done with your life.
You're pathetic! A grown-ass
man wailing like an infant!
Are ya sad now? Well, boo hoo!
You get to spend the rest
of your lives doing nothing
but eating and shitting
in this cell!
Enjoy.
It's your turn.
There's an order
to these things.
Perhaps it's a law
of human nature.
When one's time is over,
another must take on
the role that they used to play.
And thus, the world can
never be cleansed of it.
Best of luck, Hange.
Section Commander?
[inhales, exhales]
[grunts]
Uuh!
I'm sorry. Seems I made a mess.
I encountered a large cockroach.
I see. Well, as hard
as you kicked it,
I bet it learned its lesson.
It's time you filled them in.
Oh, yeah.
I guess I might as well.
So they plan to eat Eren?
[HANGE] Yeah. Eren remembered
a conversation between
Ymir and Bertholdt.
[YMIR]
You hold that against me?
I don't think so.
I mean, I don't know.
Suppose I have to believe you
didn't want to eat anyone.
Based on this, we can speculate.
Ymir used to be a mindless
Titan just like the others.
Until she consumed someone.
Someone from Bertholdt
and Reiner's group.
We've never seen a Titan
turn back into a human
by eating one before.
That said, Reiner's comrades
aren't normal humans.
And there's a
different set of rules
for humans that can
turn into Titans.
My thought is this:
If a Titan eats someone
with that power, then it'll
transform back into a human.
What's more, they'll obtain
whatever powers that human had.
In the other day's battle,
Reiner was throwing Titans
at Eren as he tried to run away.
He knew that Eren had
the power to take command
of feral Titans with his scream.
If Eren's death would've
meant that power was lost,
he wouldn't have risked it.
I think he hoped one of
those Titans would eat Eren
and take his power.
My point is, if the government
has a Titan of their own,
they'll use it to eat Eren.
Calm down. I know you
wanna get Eren back,
but going on a rampage
won't help with that.
Anyway, we're heading for
Rod Reiss' estate.
Prepare to leave at once.
[ARMIN, CONNY, SASHA, JEAN]
Sir!
[HANGE] I'll go tell Erwin
everything we've learned
about the Reiss family.
I'm sure he's waiting
to hear from us.
[LEVI]
Right.
[HANGE]
You head for Lord Reiss' estate.
I'll find you when I can.
[knocking]
Pardon, sir, but the
commander of the Garrison
has just arrived.
Pyxis?
[SOLDIER 40A] Yes, he's asking
to speak with you.
--Very well, then.
--Sir!
Forgive me for
dropping in unannounced.
But I just couldn't
stand still, you see.
I finished reading your letter.
And I have a few
thoughts of my own.
But first, I have to ask.
You are serious, right?
Yes. I have a plan
to retake Wall Maria
and to depose the government.
[PYXIS] Mm. I knew
this would happen someday.
The state could only hold
people in this cramped world
for so long before
they began to lash out.
And I knew that
when the time came,
I would have to point my gun
at the king I'm sworn to serve.
Should a certain hunch
of mine prove to be correct,
it may be possible for us
to carry out this plan
without military force.
My objective, at least,
is a bloodless coup.
Ahh. Then by all means, go on.
If such an option
is plausible, I'm for it.
Well, the catch is that
the groundwork for this
has yet to be laid out.
And if things don't go
as I think they will,
there's no plan B. I, and
everyone else, will be hanged.
Oh. Is that all?
So this is another one of
your great gambles, then.
Seems I may be a
betting man to the end.
I expect the news
to come shortly.
If you care to wait,
I'd like you to hear
a story from my childhood.
Huh?
About my father.
He was a teacher.
[CROWD murmuring]
Damn. Too bad.
Section Commander, that was--
I saw it. Keep moving!
[knocking]
--[door knob clicks]
--[door squeaks]
--Commander. It's done.
--[door thuds]
[whispering]
Reiss is the true royal house.
[ERWIN]
I thought as much.
Looks like my gamble
might pay off, Commander.
Might.
One of the First Interior
Squad just confessed.
The current king is
a pretender to the throne.
Reiss is the true royal family.
Are you sure?
I've deployed my scouts.
They're working to retrieve
Eren and Historia.
Once they're secured,
we'll declare that
Historia Reiss
is of royal blood.
And crown her as
this country's queen.
[BOTH gasp]
Knowing this is true, the ersatz
king will have no choice
but to give up the throne.
Assuming that he does, we'll
have staged a bloodless coup.
Then we'll go to the people
and expose the system
that claimed to protect them
for all its lies.
I'm convinced. You can
count on my support.
That said. We could be
in the wrong.
The final decision
is out of our hands.
You do understand that,
don't you?
I do. Yes.
[HORSE neighs]
[HANGE] Anything come
of the Reiss investigation?
I found out as much as I could.
Not much to speak of.
Just one curious incident.
Huh.
Commander Erwin!
The Interior Squad's
put out a warrant for you.
They're making a scene in
the middle of the city, sir.
Saying you had someone murdered.
What?
It would appear that the enemy
has been making
plans of their own.
Hange. Leave town at once.
[HANGE] Huh? What are you
planning to do?
[ERWIN] I need to be the face
of the Scout Regiment.
I trust you to act
at your own discretion.
Also, I've chosen
the Scouts' next leader.
And it's you. Zoë Hange.
The Scouts are in your hands.
--[door knob clicks]
--[door squeaks, thuds]
[whispers]
Hey. That's him.
[MALE CIVILIAN 40A whispers]
Erwin's here?
[CROWD whispering]
I take it you know
who this is. Right, Erwin?
[ERWIN]
That's Mr. Dimo Reeves.
He was the head of
the Reeves company.
Just yesterday,
at this exact location,
Eren Jaeger was abducted by
a group of Reeves' lackeys.
However, Reeves was hired
to do this by none other
than the Scouts themselves,
in the hopes that they might
avoid handing Eren Jaeger
over to the government.
And then, when Reeves had
outlived his usefulness,
they killed him
to stop him from talking.
The murderer is still at large.
We presume they have Jaeger.
What a convenient story
that would be.
I can see what you
scoundrels are doing.
You're trying to monopolize
Jaeger's Titan power
and keep it all for yourselves.
That type of action
violates clause six
of the Charter of Humanity.
I trust that you're
familiar with that law?
One must never
prioritize their own gain
over humanity's survival.
Am I correct?
That you are.
And because the Scout Regiment
is in violation of this law,
all Scouts must be arrested.
[FLEGEL]
Dad.
[KENNY] Maybe this'll
satisfy the fat cats.
Reeves ended up being
just as useful
against us as with us.
But we still don't have
any leads on Levi.
Like I told you, the runt's
not gonna hide forever.
When he shows, we kill him.
What do you think we should do?
--Give me a moment.
--What?
[gasps]
Get the hell away
from my husband!
When the battle
for Trost first began,
Mr. Reeves delayed
evacuation efforts
in order to preserve his wealth.
Yeah? So, what's your point?
Are you trying to say
he deserved to die?
No, I'm not. Because upon
his return to Trost,
he found it on
the verge of collapse.
And instead of abandoning it,
he planted his feet.
He helped those
who couldn't leave
by striving to revive this city.
But now, that dream
has been cut short
by a knife in the dark.
I swear this...
...I will avenge him.
[ERWIN]
My father. He was a teacher.
One day, we were
studying history.
"Faced with the annihilation
at the hands of Titans,
humanity took refuge
behind the walls,
and realized 100 years of peace.
But in this process,
we lost all records of what
humanity's earlier past
might've looked like."
That's what all of us
were taught.
Even back then,
this seemed strange to me.
And so, I asked
my father a question.
He gave me a fairly
evasive answer
and continued with
the standard lesson.
But, when we
got home that night,
he sat me down and
gave me the real answer.
He told me the
history books he received
from the government were full
of contradictions and mysteries.
He then proceeded to
tell me a theory of his.
Even as a child,
I was astounded.
There was a reason
he didn't share that theory
with the entire class, but I
wasn't smart enough to see it.
I told the other children
what he had told me.
And one day, the MPs
arrived to question me.
My father didn't
come home that night.
They said he died in
some kind of freak accident.
But I knew that wasn't true.
He'd been silenced
by the government.
One hundred seven years ago,
when humanity fled
to these walls,
the king altered
their collective memory
to make them easier to rule.
That was my father's theory.
Yes. I can see why
the first king might do that.
He must've believed that
such knowledge
would lead to civil strife.
Yes. But ever since I was
a child, I've asked myself:
Why would the government
have to kill my father
for nothing more than
getting close to the truth?
Despite the cruelty of it,
I'd hoped their motives
at least might've been noble.
But more recently, I've realized
something about these men.
What they're fighting
to protect is not humanity.
But their own gardens,
houses, and lands.
Which means, all they care
about is suppressing those
who dare to question
their authority in any way.
I no longer believe that
there was any justification
for my father's death.
He was killed by human greed.
And by the sheer stupidity
of his own son.
I can't tell you why,
but I know in my gut
that my father's words
were true.
I've made it my mission in this
life to atone to my father
by showing the world
he was right.
[MALE SOLDIER 40B]
The Scout Regiment
has murdered a civilian!
Some of them
have evaded capture!
These people are dangerous!
If you spot any of
the people on these posters,
report them immediately!
I told you, didn't I?
These are the same bastards
that unleashed a Titan here.
They destroyed half the town.
[MALE CIVILIAN 40C]
I bet they're planning to use
that freakshow Jaeger
to wipe us all out!
[JEAN] Captain,
we bought the supplies.
The MPs were
handing out these flyers.
If this is true, the Scouts
will be disbanded.
They say they'll be hunting for
us in the mountains tonight.
They're also posting guards
on all the vital roads.
No one can get
through them without a pass.
So, Captain? What now?
We need to hurry and find Eren.
He'll be fine.
They're taking him on a wagon.
That gives us one day
before they reach Reiss' estate.
And we need
every second we can get
to come up with a plan.
Captain. I hear footsteps.
Sounds like they're approaching.
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] Those who
believed in justice.
Those who protected others.
Those who gave up their lives.
The courage they showed
in our memory
is the same courage
we use to fight.
Next episode: "Trust."