I should've realized.
Of course this would happen.
Still... trusting your plan
was the only choice I had.
But why?
Armin...
Why don't you ever run?
[clattering]
[gasps]
[EREN]
A Titan?
[EREN gasps]
Damn it!
[EREN]
Just try and come closer!
Make one move to take him
and I'll slit his throat!
[EREN]
Hold on.
Those markings around his eyes.
Are they what I think?
This must be the Beast Titan.
I found you.
Eren Jaeger, right?
[growls]
[EREN] If nothing else,
I'll take him with me!
You don't look a thing
like your father.
[EREN gasps]
What?
Believe me, Eren.
I get it. I know how you feel.
The both of us are just
victims of your father.
I'm sorry, but he's
brainwashed you.
[gasps]
[EREN]
What're you talking about?
[ZEKE groans]
You're kidding.
He chased me all this way?
What a monster.
[groans] Let's call
it a draw, Levi.
We're in no shape to fight now.
Bertholdt.
I'm sorry, but this
is the end for you.
[ZEKE]
Eren.
Someday, I'll come back
and save you from this.
Huh?
[EREN]
He ran?
[LEVI grunts]
Captain!
I just used the last of my gas.
Quick, give me your gear
so I can chase him.
Right!
[LEVI]
Hurry!
[ARMIN coughs]
[EREN gasps]
[HANGE]
Reiner.
What's this metal case we found
in your left breast pocket?
Before we closed in and
chopped off your limbs,
you used what strength
you had left to grab at it.
So what's inside?
Suicide pills? A bomb?
Ow!
Sorry, Jean.
It's a letter.
A letter?
What does it say?
It's for Christa.
Ymir wrote it.
[REINER]
Whatever you do with me,
just make sure she
gets to read it.
Only after we've inspected it.
[HANGE]
Now then.
I've got lots of questions
that you could answer, but...
[JEAN gasps]
...you're a tough one.
If you don't wanna talk,
I can't make you.
So I'll ask.
Will you cooperate and tell us
everything that we want to know?
I won't.
Thank you, Reiner.
It helps to see that
you're ready for death.
[JEAN gasps]
[HANGE grunts]
Hange, wait!
We--need him alive.
So we can steal his power.
[HANGE gasps]
[ERWIN]
Pay close attention.
I'm about to explain how
we can get maximum value
from this syringe.
[ERWIN]
Using its contents,
we can steal any Titan's powers.
That goes for the Colossal,
Armored, and Beast Titans.
As for how,
we first need to defeat one
of these Intelligent Titans.
Then, we'll inject
one of our comrades,
turning them into a pure Titan.
They'll be in that mindless
state only for a brief time.
Once they consume
the captured foe,
they'll revert into a human,
but gain the power to
shift forms at will.
If this is achieved,
then not only will we gain
knowledge and a powerful weapon,
we'll also be able to bring
one of our soldiers back
from the brink of death.
Should you capture
an enemy shifter,
be sure to sever their limbs.
Once it's safe to do so,
try to locate Captain Levi.
[ERWIN]
We have only this one injection.
The captain will decide
when to use it, and on whom.
We don't know the situation
with Levi on the other side.
And we don't have the time to
go and confirm it ourselves.
These Titan powers have
exceeded our understanding
too many times.
We thought we had him before.
I refuse to underestimate
his power again.
I'll start by beheading him,
but that's not
enough on its own.
[JEAN]
This isn't like you, Hange.
[JEAN] If we back down from the
chance to cure our ignorance,
then what hope do we have
of beating the Titans
down the road?
Jean.
We need to find out all that
we can about the enemy,
or we'll lose.
Mikasa.
Yeah?
How much gas do you have left?
Not enough to fight anything.
I think I could reach Eren
and Armin, but then I'd be out.
Well that's more than I have.
[HANGE]
Find them, Mikasa.
Go and evaluate the situation.
[HANGE] Refill your gas,
retrieve the syringe from Levi,
and bring it back to me.
If you're unable to do so,
then regardless of the reason,
fire off a smoke signal.
That will be my cue
to end Reiner.
Understood.
Thank you, Hange. I--
[HANGE]
The decision was mine.
You were just a factor.
[JEAN]
Why did I speak up for him?
When it comes down
to it, am I still--?
[EREN]
Yeah! Hell yeah!
--[ARMIN wheezing]
--Armin's still breathing.
--I hear him!
Keep going!
Don't give up!
You can make it!
That's Armin?
Captain! Get the syringe!
[EREN grunts]
Turn Armin into a Titan,
and then we can have
him eat Bertholdt!
Hurry up and inject him!
[LEVI]
Right.
[gasps]
[JEAN gasps]
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[JEAN]
Hange!
[ZEKE grunts]
[JEAN grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
What the hell?
[gasps]
They're running
away with Reiner!
What now?
[gasps]
Shit!
[HANGE]
Conny!
Don't chase them!
[gasps] Huh?
Chances are,
you'd just get killed,
even if you had gas left.
[JEAN]
Son of a bitch!
This is all my fault.
He'd be dead.
He needed to die.
Why'd I open my mouth?
[HANGE] I told you,
the decision was mine.
Let's regroup with the others.
[FLOCH grunts]
[gasps]
[FLOCH]
Levi...
Captain...
I finally found you.
It's the commander.
He's hurt!
His stomach is gouged, and his
insides are all torn to shreds.
The blood just won't stop!
I thought that injection might
be able to help him, but...
...what do you think?
[EREN]
Huh...?
Captain Levi.
It's faint, but he's breathing.
Erwin.
You're alive.
You know what has to happen.
Erwin gets the shot.
[EREN growls]
You can't.
You told me you'd
use it on Armin.
[LEVI] I'm going to revive the
person who can save humanity.
[FLOCH gasps]
[ZEKE]
Reiner.
You were incredibly lucky today.
You two.
Do you have even the
faintest damn clue...
...what you're doing?
[LEVI]
It's Erwin...
...the Commander
of the Scouts...
...and you're telling
me to watch him die?
[LEVI]
There's no time for this.
Just get out of my way.
[EREN grunts]
Eren. Check your emotions.
Sorry, Captain. Can't do that.
Tell me.
Why didn't you give Armin
the injection right away?
I was thinking about Erwin.
Considering the chance
that he might be alive.
But you couldn't have known
that Floch would carry
the commander here.
There's no way you
would've seen that coming!
You aren't wrong, Eren.
But the fact remains,
he's here now.
So I'll revive him.
[EREN gasps, grunts]
[gasps]
[MIKASA screams]
[MIKASA grunting]
Hey!
[MIKASA]
He's too exhausted to stop me.
I could take it
from him by force.
You know just as well as I do.
Without Erwin's leadership,
humanity can't beat the Titans!
[FLOCH] He's right,
Mikasa. Don't be crazy!
There's too much at stake here.
[MIKASA growls]
[gasps]
No...
It's the same with Armin.
He's just as important.
Eren!
[EREN]
Think about it.
Think about what he's done.
We used his plan to take back
Trost with that boulder.
He's the one who
realized what Annie was.
It was his idea to avoid the
Titans by coming here at night!
He's the only reason we
uncovered Reiner's hiding spot,
and the only reason
we defeated Bertholdt!
We only got this far
because of Armin!
I can't save humanity,
and neither can the commander!
But Armin can!
Tell him, Mikasa!
[MIKASA grunts]
Please, Captain. Just let go.
You're just being selfish.
Erwin's our leader.
No. Shut up!
What? And why the hell should I?
Do you think you're
the only ones
who've suffered
through all this?
Not that you asked, but...
...on the other
side of that wall,
there's not a single
soldier left alive.
The Beast Titan threw
crushed boulders at everyone.
That field is soaked with
the blood of my comrades.
Commander Erwin was the
only survivor I could find.
He came up with a plan.
Found a way for us to strike
back at the Beast Titan,
and so we did.
My comrades were smashed to
bits just as he'd planned.
I'm sure the last thing
they felt was fear.
All-consuming fear...
[FLOCH] When I realized the
commander was still alive,
I almost finished
him off myself.
[FLOCH]
But then...
...I recognized that
would be a mercy.
[FLOCH]
And I thought to myself
that he ought to taste
more of this hell.
[FLOCH]
Suddenly, I understood.
[FLOCH] If we wanna stand any
chance against the Titans,
we need a devil!
I realized that's what Erwin is,
and that it's my mission
to bring him back!
That's why a coward like me
outlived the heroes around him.
Because Erwin needs to fight on!
So get out of his way right now!
Don't do it!
[MIKASA grunts]
Hange.
[MIKASA grunting]
No. Don't tell me--
No way!
It can't be.
[HANGE gasps]
No.
It isn't fair.
[MIKASA gasps]
[gasps, screams]
[HANGE]
I understand how you feel,
but most of us are dead!
We can't afford to lose
our commander, too!
The Scouts must endure!
If we lose our symbol of
hope, we lose everything!
I know that, but Armin
could help us, too.
He's special!
You're right. He has
an amazing mind.
That said, Erwin is
far more experienced,
and he's a leader.
--[HANGE groaning]
--[MIKASA sobbing]
Listen, Mikasa.
There're people I
wanna bring back, too.
Hundreds at this point.
[gasps]
Ever since I joined
up with the Scouts,
every day brought
a new farewell.
Hange, look out!
[HANGE]
But... you need to understand.
Eventually, you'll have to let
go of everyone you've ever met.
I know that's tough to accept.
It's tough for me, too.
It's hard to stay sane
living like that.
It hurts.
It really hurts.
I know.
But even so, all of us
just have to push forward.
[EREN]
Captain.
Do you... know about... the sea?
It's like a lake, but enormous.
So big that it stretches
past the horizon.
And its full of salty water.
Armin told me--
[FLOCH]
Hey! Stop making this harder!
[EREN] He told me there's
a sea beyond the walls.
He said that we'd
go there together!
Thing is, that's been our
dream since we were kids.
Only I forgot it
a long time ago!
I want to avenge my mom.
I wanna butcher all the Titans.
The only thoughts left in
my head are full of hate!
Yeah. And Armin's lost
as much as I have,
but he just isn't like me.
He cares about more
than fighting!
Everyone get out
of here right now!
I don't want Erwin to eat one
of you instead of Bertholdt.
Right. C'mon, Mikasa.
Shit. Shit!
Bye, Armin.
We'll miss you.
[ARMIN]
All right, then!
Let's start by finding the sea!
You'll see! It does exist!
[LEVI] If this dream
of yours comes true,
what will you do then?
[ERWIN]
I don't know, and I won't.
Not until it happens.
I just...
...wanted to reach that cellar.
[LEVI]
Good grief.
They're all the same.
Whining like brats
about this dream or that.
All of us had to spend our
lives drunk on somethin'.
Else we'd have no cause
to keep pushin' on.
Everyone was a
slave to somethin'.
[ARMIN]
There's more out there, though.
The sea!
Did you just--?
Excuse me...
...but how can we be sure that
there aren't other humans...
...living somewhere
far away from the walls?
[LEVI] Give up on your dream
and charge to your death.
Lead those crying children
straight to hell.
[KENNY]
We humans, we're all the same.
Every last one of us.
I'll reach the Beast
Titan and tear him apart.
Thank you.
I needed that.
[groans]
[gasps]
[BERTHOLDT screaming]
[BERTHOLDT]
Guys, please!
Help me!
[screaming]
Annie! Reiner!
[FLOCH]
I don't get it.
Captain... why?
Do you think... you can
forgive him someday?
He became a devil
'cause he had to.
We were the ones
who put him up to it.
And in the end,
when he had finally been
set free from this hell,
we were about to bring
him back for more.
But I think...
it's time we let him rest.
Erwin.
I told you I would
kill the Beast Titan,
but that'll have to wait.
He's already dead.
[gasps]
Oh.
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] After learning of
Bertholdt and Erwin's deaths,
Armin is shaken.
The path before him clear,
Eren heads for the
place his father, Grisha,
once promised to show him.
Next episode: "The Basement."