♪ Opening Song ♪
[IAN]
Defend him!
To the last man if
that's what it comes to!
Eren must reach the gate!
I don't want a single
Titan anywhere near him!
[BERTHOLDT] They're trying
to plug up the hole
with that boulder?
That's insane!
They're gambling everything!
For all they know,
if Eren gets eaten,
then their best hope'll
be gone for good.
[REINER] His death would
be a problem for us, too.
If he goes down,
I'll step in with my Titan.
[BERTHOLDT]
What if he doesn't?
We risked a lot
to make that hole.
Should we really
let him plug it?
[REINER]
Yeah, we should.
Five years we searched
for a lead like this,
and now we've finally found it.
--[MARCO] Reiner? Bertholdt?
--[BOTH gasp]
Sorry, but what were
you talking about?
You're gonna "step in
with your titan"?
And Bertholdt, you said
you made that hole?
What is this?
Uh... Marco.
Everything you just
heard was... a joke.
[MARCO]
Have you guys lost it?
This isn't like you!
Focus on the mission!
Look, there are
more Titans coming!
Let's go!
[MARCO]
Humans can turn into Titans.
I know that for a fact
because Eren did it.
[MARCO] The Colossal Titan
appeared out of nowhere,
attacked Trost, and vanished.
The best explanation is
that it's someone like Eren.
[MARCO] The same goes
for the Armored Titan.
And if they are human,
then maybe they're
hiding among us...
--[whirring]
--[gasps]
[MARCO groans]
[BERTHOLDT]
Reiner!
Reiner! What are
you doing? [groans]
Please--no.
Say it's a joke.
[REINER]
Wish I could, Marco.
Problem is, you're too damn
sharp for that to fool you.
[gasps] Somebody help--!
[ANNIE grunts]
[panting]
[MARCO]
Annie! You gotta help me!
[ANNIE]
What's going on here?
Reiner's acting crazy!
Get him off me!
He heard me and
Bertholdt talking.
If we let him live,
he'll expose us.
[gasping] You shitheads.
What the hell?
[gasps]
[BERTHOLDT, REINER gasp]
[BERTHOLDT]
A Titan! It's coming this way!
[MARCO grunts]
Annie! Take off
Marco's ODM gear!
Huh?
[ANNIE gasps]
--Do it now!
--[MARCO gasps]
[ANNIE]
Wait, why should I have to?
[REINER] Back there, you risked
your life to save Conny.
I saw you.
Why'd you put yourself
in danger for him?
Seems to me you're becoming
sympathetic towards the enemy.
You wanna convince me I'm wrong,
then now's the time to do it!
Think of your father.
He's waiting for
you to come home.
If you and he are any different
than the filth
within these walls,
then prove it, here and now!
Hey! It's almost on top of us!
Annie!
[ANNIE growls, grunts]
[screams]
What're you doing?
Annie! I thought
we were comrades!
Please! Please!
--[ANNIE gasps]
--I don't wanna die here!
Don't kill me!
[MARCO sobbing]
[REINER]
You did well, Annie.
This is what makes us warriors.
[ANNIE]
Reiner. Do we move out?
Not yet.
We have to let them
gather up first.
[MARCO]
I see.
They waited 'cause they
want the Titans to win.
[MARCO]
Just wait.
Why do this?
Why are you in such
a hurry to kill me?
I don't get it.
How come?
Why aren't you even
willing to talk to me?
Why?!
[ALL gasp]
[MARCO screaming]
[REINER]
Hey. Why...?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
Why is Marco... being devoured?
[MAN]
Like I said.
I'm sure Annie's doing fine.
She's certainly isn't
getting tortured.
Calm down and consider
how unlikely that sounds.
If they so much as scratch her,
she'll turn into a monster
that can take on an army
all by itself.
Don't forget, this is Annie
we're talking about here.
I bet she's hiding somewhere,
practicing her
kicks and what not.
She's fine.
Still, there's no doubt that
her identity was revealed.
Annie's smart, but...
[MAN sighs] It doesn't sound
like you're fully committed.
[BOTH gasp]
The hell's your problem?
I thought that all three
of us came to an agreement.
Did I go to all that
trouble for nothing?
We can fight again
if you want to.
That said,
the next time that
you lose to me,
I'll make you give up your
armor to another warrior.
What? No.
I'll do as you tell me to.
[MAN]
Then pull yourselves together.
We have one objective.
Recover the Coordinate.
Do that, and we can bring
this cursed history to an end.
[MAN]
It's gone on too long.
We can be the ones to end this.
So let's do it.
Understood, sir.
Till this is done,
I will keep Annie
out of my head.
This is a living hell,
but we shouldn't put
anyone else through it.
You're right.
This needs to end.
It's settled then.
[CART TITAN]
War Chief Zeke.
Enemy forces are approaching.
They're at the foot
of the mountain.
[ZEKE]
My brave warriors.
With this final battle,
we'll finish our mission
once and for all.
[ZEKE groans]
Hot!
Ready?
Yeah.
[REINER]
Bertholdt.
I've told you this plenty,
but you and I'll be in
separate positions,
so try thinking on your
own for once, all right?
[BERTHOLDT]
Uh, right.
[REINER] You don't always
have to wait for my signal.
[BERTHOLDT]
Yeah. I know that.
You're supposed to have
the most powerful ability
out of all of us,
but you never use it
unless your told.
Honestly, I never
saw you as reliable.
I know that, too.
Not until today.
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
We're gonna finish
this here, yeah?
That's right.
And there's nothing
they can do to stop us.
[REINER]
Hold onto that attitude
until you're back
with your beloved.
[BERTHOLDT] Huh? I-I don't
know what you're talking about.
[REINER] Annie's pretty cold,
but save her from a dungeon
and she just might
see you with new eyes.
Hell, if you play
your cards right,
she might mistake
you for a knight.
Oh, and as for Christa.
We're gonna save
her no matter what.
That's the promise we made Ymir.
Yeah. We'll find a way.
I'll see ya.
Don't let me down, 'kay?
I've got your back.
[BERTHOLDT] It's been a while
since I heard Reiner transform,
but he still hasn't signaled.
Why?
Did something go
wrong out there?
[SCOUTS cheering]
[SCOUT 52A]
We did it!
[SCOUT 52B]
We blew that bastard's head off!
The Armored Titan
just bit the dust!
[SCOUT 52E] We sent him straight
to hell. Good riddance!
Ha... ha... We pulled it off.
You were a serious pain
in the ass for us.
Serves you right! You scumbag!
--[CONNY, SASHA crying]
--[gasps]
[growls]
What the hell are
you crying for?
Stop! Get up!
We still have work to do!
Don't cry for him!
He would've done
the same thing to us!
[EREN gasps]
This isn't over!
We'll hit him with another
volley just to be sure.
[MIKASA gasps]
You okay?
I guess so.
It's not like we
could negotiate.
[MIKASA gasps]
[ARMIN]
Their side has the knowledge.
They make us look just as
ignorant as we are weak.
We don't have the ability
to capture someone
who can turn into
a Titan on a whim.
Which means... there was
nothing we could do.
[MIKASA gasps]
[roaring]
[ARMIN gasps]
[EREN gasps]
[ERWIN]
Was that--?
That's the signal! It's time!
[BOTH gasp]
[HANGE]
Use your Thunder Spears!
If we want him dead, we'll have
to destroy his whole body!
[ARMIN]
That scream just now...
Was it for Bertholdt?
[gasps]
Hange, wait!
We need to fall back for now!
See that barrel?
I'm sure Bertholdt's inside!
If he transforms,
we're done for!
[BERTHOLDT]
C'mon, Reiner! Hang in there!
I'm coming!
[ERWIN]
They got us.
Shit!
Everyone, move away
from the Armored Titan!
The Colossal Titan is
falling towards us right now!
[ARMIN]
No.
Even at this distance...
...we'll all be
caught in the blast!
[BERTHOLDT]
Ground's pretty close.
It's now or never.
I'll blow this
whole place to hell!
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
Reiner!
[BERTHOLDT]
Are you--?
No way.
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
What the--?
He's still alive!
He must have transferred
his consciousness
throughout his entire
nervous system.
[BERTHOLDT]
We talked about it,
but only as a last resort.
To think that he would
actually need to.
[BERTHOLDT] It's hard to believe
they cornered you like this.
Damn it.
[BERTHOLDT]
Reiner.
I need you to do
something for me.
You're gonna have to
move just a little bit.
And if you can't,
then I'm sorry.
Prepare for the worst.
I'm ending this war.
[HANGE sighs]
[HANGE]
Here we go.
Our mission's primary objective
just fell straight
into our laps.
You could call this
a stroke of luck.
[MOBLIT gasps]
Hey! Look!
Someone's coming our way!
It's Bertholdt!
[HANGE]
The plan is as follows!
Armin, you take
command of Levi Squad.
Protect Eren!
Everyone else
should come with me.
We've got two targets
to eliminate!
[SCOUTS]
Right!
[ARMIN]
Hold on!
What? Why?
This is the only chance
we'll get to negotiate!
[grunts] Stop, Bertholdt!
Just wait a minute!
[EREN]
Armin.
What are you trying to achieve?
[ARMIN inhales]
We don't have to fight!
Let's talk this over!
[inhales]
[BERTHOLDT]
If I agree to talk,
would you all be willing
to lay down and die?
[gasps]
[BERTHOLDT]
We only want two simple things!
Eren Jaeger, and the death
of everyone in the walls!
That's the harsh truth
of our situation.
Understand?
All of your fates
have been decided!
What? And who is it
that decided that?
[BERTHOLDT]
I did.
[gasps]
What was that?
It was me, Armin!
I decided your lives
should end here and now!
That's a real shame, Bertholdt.
See, I was hoping
I'd finally get to stop
hearing Annie scream!
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
[ARMIN] There's only one
person who can save her
from the savages in
the Military Police,
and that's you!
If you don't, she'll
be fed to the pigs!
[BERTHOLDT]
Fine by me!
[gasps]
[BERTHOLDT]
Let them feed Annie to the pigs!
If they actually
have her, that is!
[ARMIN gasps]
[BERTHOLDT]
What's the rush, Armin?
Didn't you wanna "talk"?
[ARMIN grunts]
Bet you thought that
by bringing up Annie,
you could make me lose
my cool, like last time.
You thought I was still the
timid fool you once knew,
and that you could trick me
into letting my guard down!
Stay back, Eren.
You get it, don't you?
Your chances of beating
him are damn slim.
This isn't your fight yet.
[EREN]
Shit.
Armin, why?
I know what this is.
You're just buying
time, aren't you?
Half your comrades'll
surround me.
And while I'm distracted,
the rest'll go and
finish killing Reiner.
I can tell I'm right.
Look at the way you're shaking.
You're scared outta
your mind, aren't you?
If you knew that much,
then why're you talking
to me in the first place?
Because I needed to know...
...if when I faced
all of you this time,
I'd start crying and beg you to
put me out of my misery again.
[BERTHOLDT]
But...
...it seems like I'm fine now.
You'll always be
my dear comrades,
right up until I've killed you.
But why?
Do you actually believe that
we're the spawn of the devil?
[BERTHOLDT]
No.
None of you did anything wrong.
I know you aren't devils.
Even so, you can't be
permitted to live.
That's just how it is.
[MIKASA grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[ARMIN]
Mikasa!
--[BERTHOLDT grunts]
--[ARMIN gasps]
[MIKASA grunts]
[BERTHOLDT grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[MIKASA]
Don't do it. We can't chase him.
There's no telling when
he'll choose to transform.
If we don't keep our distance,
we'll just get caught
in the explosion.
[ARMIN] I don't think Bertholdt
intends to do that just yet.
He must've seen how badly
wounded Reiner is.
Transforming now would
probably kill him.
Our best bet is to
take Reiner hostage
and fight Bertholdt
with our blades.
That'd make sense, but...
From the look of him,
it seemed like he had a plan.
And not only that.
He seemed more
determined than before.
Almost like an entirely
different person.
[ARMIN]
Yeah. I saw it, too.
Hurry! The Armored
Titan is weak!
We just have to
finish him! Uh--
[SCOUT 52D gasps]
[SCOUT 52D]
His nape's to the ground now.
What're we supposed to do?
[BERTHOLDT]
This sure is a peculiar feeling.
I'm not scared at all, for once.
And I see everything clearly.
I know... that no
matter what happens,
I can accept how this ends.
Yeah. No one's
in the wrong here.
There was nothing to be done.
[BERTHOLDT]
We had no choice in all this.
Because this world...
is just that cruel.
[HANGE]
He's going up! Don't tell me--!
[MOBLIT] But, if he transforms,
he'll kill Reiner, too!
We need to get out of here!
Hange, look out!
[HANGE gasps]
[ALL grunting]
[JEAN]
Are you guys alive?
[CONNY]
Hell if I know! Are you?
[SASHA]
I'm fine. Hangin' in there.
Mikasa! Armin!
You two okay?
Yeah, it missed us.
Where's Hange Squad?
They were right
underneath the blast zone.
[SASHA, CONNY, JEAN gasp]
Are you saying...
[heartbeat]
[JEAN]
...the only ones who survived...
...are the six of us?
Oh, no.
[JEAN grunts]
Armin! What do we do now?
We can't just wait to get
flattened by burning houses!
[MIKASA]
Hey.
You're in command now, Armin.
We'll follow you to the end.
[ARMIN gasps]
[ARMIN]
We...
We retreat.
Fall back to the commander
and request new orders.
To beat the Colossal Titan in a
battle of attrition as planned,
we have to keep our distance.
[JEAN]
That was the plan, but think.
If we let the Colossal
Titan reach the wall,
the others'll be finished.
[ARMIN gasps]
[JEAN] He'll spread that fire
to the houses past the gate.
Our other squads'll be trapped
between the Titans
and the flames.
[ARMIN gasps]
You're right.
Our only hope is to beat
Bertholdt right now.
And we won't get help.
We have to do it with
the people we have here.
[EREN growls]
[SASHA gasps]
Hey, Armin!
Your orders? C'mon!
What should we do?
I bet you're pleased
with yourself.
Your plan's working so far.
What will you do next?
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] The Colossal
Titan makes its move,
setting Shiganshina ablaze.
Meanwhile, Erwin and the others
are forced into a
desperate charge.
[NARRATOR]
Next episode: "Perfect Game."