[NARRATOR]
Before it's fall,
Wall Maria contained a
third of what usable land
remained to humanity.
Five years ago, when humanity
lost this territory,
from behind their
last two walls,
the people realized something.
Humankind...
is fated to become extinct.
[NARRATOR]
Defeat was certain.
The blade of despair
pierced our hearts.
I'm gonna put a stop to this.
I'll kill them all.
Every last one.
[NARRATOR] But then, someone
grasped that blade and wrenched,
turned sorrow to rage,
and lashed out at the Titans,
striking the monsters down
with earth-shaking force.
When humanity first saw this,
what was in their hearts then?
In some, a stalwart pride.
In others, newfound hope.
And some beat with that
first warrior's rage.
[NARRATOR] So, if Wall
Maria were taken back,
what would the people feel then?
[NARRATOR] Would they finally
start to believe in mankind?
In the fact that we
deserve to live?
[ERWIN]
Scouts, move out!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Would they see at last
that our fates are
for us to decide?
Would it be enough
to give them faith?
[NARRATOR] If we could reach
Wall Maria and take it back.
♪ Opening Song ♪
--[MALE SOLDIER 50A gasps]
--Huh?
[horse neighs]
[MALE SOLDIER 50B]
Whoa. Steady.
Slow down.
Make sure the ground is lit.
[MALE SOLDIER 50B]
Right. Sorry, sir.
Will we get there soon?
It's just about dawn.
Well, once we get
over this mountain,
Shiganshina should be close by.
I'm sorry that you got
stuck with my horse.
Don't worry about it.
You should be
saving your energy.
Yeah, I get it, but still.
She's right, Eren.
We need you at your best.
[JEAN]
Don't say his name, dumbass.
[CONNY gasps]
Sorry, I forgot.
Act as though we're
surrounded by enemies.
Always.
[gasps]
[JEAN]
Titan on the left!
Everyone halt!
Light up the area!
[swords clank]
[HANGE]
It's all right.
Pretty sure he's asleep.
Doesn't look like this
is one of the new types
that can move around
at night. [chuckles]
Well isn't that a shame?
Leave him be.
[swords clank]
[HANGE sighs]
I can't believe we had to get
that close to notice the thing.
[HANGE] Yeah,
I'm with you on that point.
But it's worth it.
The moonless night
is protecting us.
Light from the moon is really
just reflected sunlight.
And from what we can tell,
that miniscule amount
of reflected light
is all that these new
Titans need to move.
It's good that we're using
the new moon's cover.
There's no guarantee that we
won't have a repeat of before.
For all we know,
that sleeper might've been
a moonlight Titan himself.
Maybe we can
capture one someday!
[EREN]
I'm shaking.
Why?
What am I scared of?
[EREN]
Shit.
What if I screw this up
because of my nerves?
What'll happen?
We'll never get a chance
like this again.
If we fail,
the hopes of countless
people will be crushed.
And through some twist
of fate, it's all on me.
How? How can I save humanity?
I'm useless.
I'm nobody.
[EREN gasps]
Are you okay?
[ARMIN]
What's wrong? You're shaking.
Are you scared?
Huh? No!
Of course I'm not scared.
But... look at your hand.
Seems like nerves to me.
This is just 'cause
it's cold out here!
I feel like my hand's
gonna freeze off.
Is that all it is?
I've been shaking a bit, too.
And I'm terrified.
Just look at me.
I can't really tell if you've
ever been afraid of Titans.
That fear is all-consuming
for most people.
It was for me.
The first time I saw
a Titan in the flesh,
I was so frightened
I couldn't move.
Yeah.
I was gonna die.
Then you came and pulled me
out of a Titan's mouth.
But how did you do it?
Where did you find the strength?
I had a flashback...
...to the day that you
showed me your parent's book.
[EREN]
Before then,
I'd never even considered
the world beyond the walls.
I would just spend my days
staring up at the clouds.
[EREN]
But then, I heard your story,
and saw the look in your eyes.
[EREN] They were filled
with this amazing dream.
Like nothing I'd
known for myself.
That's the day I realized
that I had never been free.
The world was as vast
as our cage was small.
Those monsters had
stolen it from us.
Once I realized that,
I couldn't forgive them.
Couldn't tell you why, but...
...when I think of
that lost freedom...
[EREN]
...I feel strong.
Fearless, in a way.
Thanks for that, Armin.
I'm good now.
[ARMIN]
Mm.
Know what?
This time next year?
I bet we'll be
looking out at the sea.
--[MIKASA gasps]
--[water running]
This area. It's familiar.
[MIKASA] I think...
we came here for firewood.
[EREN gasps]
[MALE SOLDIER 50C]
I see the foot of the mountain!
[ALL gasp]
There are signs
of a trail ahead!
Well, looks like we're close.
I'm pretty sure I
can hear the river.
We made it back.
After all that's happened.
[ARMIN] This is the
first time we've seen it
since we fled as kids.
[ARMIN]
Our hometown.
Shiganshina.
There could be Titans anywhere,
so keep your guard up!
This operation has
officially begun!
All troops, switch to ODM gear!
[ERWIN] We must seal
the gate to Wall Maria
and the one to
the outside world.
With that achieved,
Shiganshina will be isolated,
and we can kill
the Titans inside.
The enemy will predict this plan
and counter it
by targeting Eren.
But...
[ERWIN]
...all 100 of our soldiers
will keep their faces
covered with hoods.
[ERWIN] By the time the
foe can locate Eren,
he'll have plugged up
the outer gate.
[EREN grunts]
[gasps]
[ARMIN, MIKASA gasp]
--[LEVI] Don't stop!
--[gasps]
You get to that outer gate!
Right!
[ARMIN gasps]
[ARMIN]
Ashes.
From a kicked-out fire?
[ARMIN grunts]
[ARMIN]
They're here and they're close.
Bertholdt and Reiner!
[EREN] My old house
is right around here.
We're so close...
...to everything we left behind.
[gasps]
[EREN]
It's fine.
I'm taking it back.
[HANGE] I know we're
overdue for some luck,
but how have we not
seen any Titans yet?
We still have to continue.
Right.
We have no cause to call it off.
[EREN grunts]
[EREN]
I can do this!
No...
We can do this!
[EREN]
Because we're special,
for no other reason than
the fact that we were born!
We will be free!
[ALL gasp]
[EREN grunts, yells]
[EREN groans, gasps]
The enemy could
strike any second!
Stay on the lookout!
Right!
--[MIKASA, EREN grunt]
--[HANGE] Eren!
Is your ODM gear secure?
[EREN grunts]
It's fine.
That said, I did manage
to shake off my cloak.
[gasps]
[EREN]
Thank you.
How's it look?
[MALE SOLDIER 50E]
Looks good over here!
[MALE SOLDIER 50F]
Yeah, our end's plugged, too!
We pulled it off. Huh.
Eren, are you okay?
Not even tired.
All that training's paid off.
[HANGE]
We shouldn't waste time then.
Everyone, head for
the inner gate!
And keep your faces hidden!
Did I actually seal that gate?
Seemed too easy.
You did it. I saw you.
Try to have faith in
your own strength.
[EREN]
I finally took it back.
--[LEVI] We're not finished.
--[EREN gasps]
[LEVI] You can plug
the gates all you want,
but they can just
break them again later.
Until we've killed
Reiner, Bertholdt,
and whoever else
may be with them,
the operation to retake
Wall Maria won't be over.
Yeah.
I'm well aware.
[DIRK] The outer gate was
closed off successfully,
but something feels wrong here.
The enemy should've
attacked by now.
Right, Erwin?
So why haven't we seen
a single Titan yet?
Is it possible that they just
weren't ready to fight us?
We can hope, but considering
what Arlelt found...
--[whirring]
--[BOTH gasp]
[ARMIN grunts]
I looked into it.
It's clear that someone
was camping on the wall.
I found cups and a
cold pot on the ground,
near where I
spotted those ashes.
They were drinking
something like black tea.
[ARMIN sniffs]
[ARMIN]
What was in here?
It smells good.
[ARMIN]
There were three cups,
and they all had the same
black liquid in the bottom.
So I'd say there were three
people camping up here at least.
Wait. There's a third?
Was the pot completely
cool to the touch?
Yes.
That's troubling.
Agreed.
Huh? Why's that?
We charged here at
full speed on horseback.
Even switched to ODM gear.
Had they noticed our approach
by sight, or perhaps by sound,
they couldn't have had more
than two minutes to react.
But a pot over flame
wouldn't have cooled
in that short of time.
[DIRK gasps]
[ERWIN] They had to have
known that we were coming
for five minutes or more.
Which tells me they've
had plenty of time
to prepare for our arrival.
There's no way.
How'd they know?
Well, it's possible
that they had a scout
in addition to the
three on the wall.
Yeah.
We should assume we
have many enemies
and that they could be anywhere.
You need to sharpen your focus
on the enemies that are nearby.
I trust you.
With that mind of yours,
you've saved us from
disaster countless times.
Now do it again.
We're in dire need of your help.
[gasps]
You can take as many
soldiers as you need.
If the enemy's hiding near
the inner gate, find them.
[ERWIN] As of now, you will
obey Armin Arlelt's commands.
--[ARMIN gasps]
--He'll tell you how to proceed.
[SOLDIERS grunt]
Uh...
[SOLDIERS]
Understood!
We searched the wall's
perimeter thoroughly!
What are your
instructions, Arlelt?
We'll send one group to
each side of the wall.
Search the interiors of any
buildings near the gate!
If you find something,
fire off an acoustic shell!
[ARMIN gasps]
Does... that work for you?
[SOLDIERS]
Understood!
Another gamble of yours?
No. Arlelt's proven himself.
He's one of our
greatest weapons.
That I know.
[DIRK] Eren's on his way
to plug the inner gate.
What now?
Should we halt the operation
till we find the enemy?
We continue.
We'll lose a prolonged
campaign in enemy territory.
To prevail, our only chance
is to win a decisive battle.
With that in mind,
even if all has
gone according to the
enemy's plan thus far,
we simply have to deal with it.
In any case,
they aren't the only ones
who are hiding something.
[ARMIN]
What do I do?
Eren's on his way to
seal the inner gate.
If the enemy's here, we need to
find them before he does it.
[gasps]
[ARMIN]
Why would they have let us
plug the outer breach
without a fight?
Why can't we find them no
matter how much we search?
[ARMIN]
They knew we'd come.
They must've!
If this is a trap...
If we fail here...
...then it'll really
be over for us.
They always catch us off-guard
by using Titans and their powers
in ways we can't predict.
And they always
have the advantage,
because they know so much more
about Titans than we do!
[ARMIN gasps]
[ARMIN]
Hold on.
[ARMIN gasping]
[ARMIN grunts]
[FEMALE SOLDIER 50A gasps]
[MALE SOLDIER 50H gasps]
[MALE SOLDIER 50G] Did you
find them, Arlelt? Where?
[ARMIN]
The walls!
Everyone scour the walls!
But we already searched
all around them!
There isn't anywhere
to hide on the walls!
[ARMIN]
Check inside them!
--[SOLDIERS gasp]
--[ERWIN gasps]
[FEMALE SOLDIER 50A]
Inside the walls?
Yes!
Look for a small cavity that
someone could hide out in.
It may be covered.
How do you know
that this exists?
It's a hunch.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Damn it! Do you have any idea
what kind of situation we're in?
We don't have time to
waste on your hunches!
But--just think about it!
The enemy always
gets the better of us
by using Titan powers in ways
we could never have imagined!
If we constrain ourselves
to normal tactical reasoning,
then we'll never be able
to gain the upper hand!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[ARMIN gasps]
[MALE SOLDIER 50I] That's the
signal to halt the mission!
Everyone scatter and
stand by on top of the wall!
[SOLDIERS]
Understood!
[ERWIN]
There are times to be strict
and times to be flexible.
Uphold the principles
of your vows.
Do what it takes to win.
Follow the chain of command
and keep your eyes fixed
on the path to victory.
[grunts] Form two groups again
and check the wall's surface!
Start your search
above the gate!
Go! Quickly!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Uh...
[SOLDIERS]
Right!
[CONNY]
What are they doing?
Is this safe?
Feel like a sitting duck.
I don't know,
but this doesn't seem like
much of a surprise attack.
I wonder.
Did Armin figure something out?
[ARMIN] A position they'll
be able to react from,
no matter when
Eren might appear.
A position from which they can
see everything that happens.
If there's a hiding
spot like that,
then it must be in the walls.
Assuming the enemy doesn't know
that we're aware of
the Titans in the wall,
they'd have every
reason to think
this would take us by surprise.
It all adds up.
[gasps, grunts]
--[gunshot]
--[ARMIN gasps]
Right here!
This part of the wall is hollow!
--[MALE SOLDIER 50H gasps]
--[REINER grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[ARMIN gasps]
[ARMIN]
Reiner!
[gasps]
[REINER groans]
[LEVI grunting]
[REINER grunts]
[gasps, grunts]
[LEVI grunts]
Shit!
[ARMIN]
Captain?
[LEVI]
What're these guys made of?
A blade through the neck and
the bastard still won't die!
[yells]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
Keep your eyes open!
We still need to find
his allies! [gasps]
[ERWIN gasps]
Incoming boulder!
Get down!
[MARLO grunts, gasps]
[MARLO]
What the--?
Looks like he missed.
Not so.
That was a well-placed shot.
He blocked off the entrance.
There's no riding
through it now.
[ERWIN]
They have us all but surrounded.
They plan to target our horses,
block our escape routes,
and slaughter us.
The enemy hopes for
the same thing we do--
to end this conflict
once and for all.
It's our side or theirs now.
We can let the Titans crush us,
or bring them crashing down.
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] A massive horde of
Titans attacks out of nowhere.
As the Scout Regiment
fights back,
Eren finds an
obstacle in his path.
A former friend
turned bitter foe.
Next episode: "Thunder Spears."