[LEVI]
Guess what?
This means we finally
have a real shot
at plugging the
hole in Wall Maria.
[gasps]
[ARMIN] The Scout Regiment
hurries its preparations
for the mission to
retake Wall Maria.
[HANGE]
Ooh!
[BOTH gasp]
[HANGE]
Hell yeah!
We did it, Eren!
Eren?
[EREN]
I'm fine.
Let's just make these
weapons quickly,
and then go to Shiganshina.
[KENNY]
Seems if I just stick myself,
I'll turn into a big,
strong Titan.
[ARMIN]
Then came another surprise.
One more thing
with the potential
to shape the fate of humanity.
Looks like I'm late. Sorry.
Have any luck?
Were you able to establish
what's in the container?
[HANGE] We have a vague
idea, but unfortunately,
with our technology, I'm afraid
we can't dig much deeper.
Like we've heard from
Eren and Historia,
it seems to originate from
some sort of human body fluid.
However, it vaporizes
when exposed to air,
making further analysis
virtually impossible to perform.
Whoever made it must
have had technology
far superior to ours.
I can't imagine how
the Reiss family
could've managed to do it.
[ZACHARY]
Hmm...
[PYXIS] In that case,
rather than tamper with it,
we should put it to use
for our current objective.
But to whom do we entrust it?
To you, Erwin?
No. With my wound,
I would be a poor choice.
This syringe, it belongs in
the hands of one of our elite.
Someone with the best
odds of survival.
Levi, will you accept it?
If it's an order, just say so.
Why even bother asking?
When we need to use this,
there may not be time to plan.
We'll be relying on you
to make a decision swiftly,
and with little deliberation.
Judging when to
use it, and on whom,
will be your responsibility.
Will you accept it?
If this dream of
yours comes true,
what will you do then?
[ERWIN]
I don't know, and I won't.
Not until it happens.
I see.
All right. I'll do it.
[ZACHARY]
Hmm...
Now then, I'd like to
discuss that work of mine.
As you know, I'm hoping
to unveil it soon.
Have you given it any thought?
You mean you still
haven't given up on that?
If the public were to see
such a repulsive display,
whatever trust they have in
the military would evaporate.
[ZACHARY] You don't know
art when you see it.
♪ Opening Song ♪
You spoke to Sadies,
and based on what he told you,
it seems that Grisha
Jaeger is a human
who came from outside the walls.
Yes, and like the others,
Annie, Reiner, and Bertholdt,
it appears he also had
the Power of the Titans.
But where those three
sought to undermine it,
he was supportive of
humanity within the walls.
If he was really that supportive
of the Scouts and what we do,
maybe he coulda thrown a bit
more information our way.
[HANGE]
I wonder.
From the moment he
entered the walls,
he was searching for
the royal family.
A heavy burden to
shoulder alone.
If you ask me,
that's not something you do
unless you have an iron will
and incredible resolve.
And let's not forget,
that same man later wanted
to show his young son,
eager to join the Scouts,
something important.
Staring death in the face,
he said the truth of it all
was there, in the cellar.
What's down there?
What was he hiding?
[ERWIN]
Things which mustn't be said.
[ERWIN] No. Things
which can't be spoken.
Things he couldn't say,
even if he wanted to.
That which the First Reiss King
wiped from our consciousness.
Memories of our world.
At least, that's my hope.
But speculating more won't
accomplish anything.
The final preparations
are now complete.
The operation to retake
Wall Maria begins in two days.
Wanna know what's
in that cellar?
Let's go see for ourselves.
We're Scouts. That's what we do.
I'll leave it to you
to alert your squads.
[CLARK] Right. We'll keep
it quiet for now, though.
[HAROLD] I think our
troops deserve some meat
on a day like this.
[DIRK]
Good idea.
Gotta show those kids the
adults can be counted on.
What about Commandant Sadies
keeping important
secrets from us.
[HANGE] Forget it. We don't
have time to deal with that now.
[MARLENE]
You must be so disappointed.
You used to adore him!
[HANGE]
Shut up!
[ERWIN]
What is it, Levi?
This may sound impatient,
but what do you think you'll
do after retaking Wall Maria?
I'm guessing a defense plan
comes first, but after that?
What's next?
Eliminating threats.
Outside the walls,
there seems to be someone
hoping that Titans
will eat us all,
down to the last person.
As to who, well,
if we have any luck,
we'll find that answer
in the cellar.
A full plan will have to wait.
First we need to see
what's in that room.
You realize I'm asking this now
because you might
not live that long.
You're not exactly as
spry as you used to be.
Let Hange call the
shots on this mission.
In your shape, you'll
only be dead weight.
You sit back and wait
for the good news.
We'll tell the others
I argued till you gave in.
Which I will, so why not make
this easier on both of us?
What do you say?
[ERWIN]
No.
Do what you need to.
Use me as bait.
The chain of command
still remains.
If I'm gone, then Hange.
If Hange's gone, the next.
It's true this operation
will be extremely dangerous,
but it will also be the most
important one in human history.
That's why I've gone
to such lengths.
This is my plan, Levi.
Without me leading you,
you're less likely to succeed.
That's true. Without you,
the operation might fail.
But if you bite the dust out
there, we're really screwed.
So just stay safe at your desk
and keep using
that head of yours.
As far as I'm concerned,
that's the last thing
the Titans would want,
and the best weapon
that humanity's got.
[ERWIN]
No, you're wrong.
Our best option is for
me to gamble it all
on the plan that I--
Okay, that's enough.
Stop right there.
Any more of those
noble-ass excuses,
and I'm gonna break
both your damn legs.
Not too badly.
They'll heal just fine, but
you'll be way too busted up
to even think about joining
us on the operation.
And it'll be a bitch
to get to the toilet.
[ERWIN chuckles]
Don't like that idea much.
Normally, I'd agree with you.
A wounded soldier should
stay off the battlefield.
However...
That may be the day we learn
the truth about our world,
and I'll be damned if
I'm going to miss it.
Being there is that important?
More than your legs?
Yes.
More than humanity's victory?
[ERWIN]
Yes.
I see.
Fine, Erwin.
In that case, I'll
trust your judgment.
[HAROLD]
This may be a special night,
but we don't need the
public knowing our plans.
So, behave like the
disciplined soldiers you are.
What? No way.
Is that...? It is.
It's meat.
[SASHA gasps]
Am I dreaming?
All right. Here's to the
re-taking of Wall Maria.
A toast!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[HAROLD]
Huh? Wait!
Calm down! Everyone'll
get some, okay?
Hey! A piece that
big counts as two!
You're crazy!
Well, I'm worth two of
you on the battlefield,
so I think I should
get your portion!
Like hell!
What the hell do you think
you're doing, potato girl?
No way are we gonna
let you pull this shit!
Drop the meat, Sasha.
Come on, I really don't
wanna have to kill you.
You can't eat the whole
thing alone, you pig!
Ah! You're eating me!
My hand! My hand!
Sasha! That meat is Jean!
We don't eat our friends, okay?
[MARLO] What, does the Scout
Regiment never get any meat?
Really? That's just sad--
[MARLO grunts]
Conny, would you just
knock her out already?
I'm trying!
It's like her mind's shut down,
but she's still moving somehow!
[DIRK] Hey, I think
we've got casualties.
[HANGE] Whose brilliant idea
was it to serve meat, again?
[HAROLD] Well, I guess now
we know what happens
when we blow the whole food
budget for two months
on one night of celebrating.
[EREN]
That should do it.
[CONNY]
She finally wore herself out.
Jeez, can you
believe this freak?
It's crazy to think
that she once offered
to share meat with everybody.
What? She did?
Yeah, four months ago,
when we were
servicing the cannons.
I totally just helped myself
to the Officer's Pantry.
[ALL gasp]
[SASHA]
It'll be fine.
Just look at it this way.
Pretty soon, we'll take back all
the room we need for livestock.
[CONNY]
They're gonna get in.
They're gonna get in!
[EREN]
He's gone!
[BERTHOLDT] In the moment,
I felt sorry for you.
[CONNY]
Hey.
It's hard to believe that
it's only been four months.
Yeah, it's kinda crazy.
But think, that's all it took
for us to make Levi Squad.
How's that for
climbin' the ranks?
[EREN] It's all because
you're a genius.
Damn straight I am.
[EREN] Come on. Let's eat
before it gets cold.
[SASHA yells]
[JEAN]
Don't you get it?
You've got no experience.
That's why you're in
the rear guard, rookie.
[MARLO]
I may be less knowledgeable
than the rest of you,
but isn't the vanguard
the best place to learn
how the enemy moves?
What's this?
You think that you can lecture
a veteran about self-sacrifice?
Isn't that what
makes us effective?
Being willing to put
ourselves in harm's way?
Listen, everyone starts
out as a recruit, okay?
If we throw recruits into
battle like cannon fodder,
then they'll all be
too dead to learn.
And that's why, for now,
it's your job to watch
and learn from the rear.
So you can make it
back in one piece.
The ones who really suck
are the suicidal maniacs
who think the only way to
fight is to charge in blind.
Right?
Are you talkin' about
somebody in particular?
Yeah, I'm looking right
at him. Suicidal maniac.
You see, the funny thing is
that I recently discovered
that I'm actually a
pretty normal person.
So, hey, if that's how
you really see me,
then maybe you're just
a coward, Jean.
Right?
You think you're so cool,
don't you, you piece of shit?
That's a pretty
shaggy-looking mane
you're growing
there, horse face!
What's with those two?
Try not to kill each other.
You jerk!
[EREN]
You're gonna rip my shirt!
What the hell are
those two doing?
[JEAN]
You bastard!
[SOLDIER 49A]
Show 'em what you've got!
[SOLDIER 49B]
He's losing ground!
It looks like we've
got a fight.
I told the idiots to behave.
But seriously.
If you didn't have Titan powers,
you'd be dead ten times over.
Although, I guess Mikasa
would've swooped in every time
to save your worthless ass.
You so eager to die?
Fine, then I'll kill you!
Yeah? Okay.
Give it your best shot!
You oughta start
showin' your mom
some more respect, Jean-boy!
Would you forget that?
Never!
Should we let them keep going?
[EREN]
Stupid horse face!
I think it's fine.
[EREN, JEAN panting]
[EREN]
Why?
Why isn't anybody stopping us?
[JEAN]
How long's this gonna go on?
Shit. I think I'm gonna
barf up that meat.
[LEVI]
Hey.
[LEVI, JEAN groaning]
[LEVI]
That's enough celebrating.
Go to bed.
[JEAN retches]
And clean that up.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[SASHA yelling]
[EREN]
Ahh...
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but shouldn't you guys
watch out for me more?
[ARMIN] Considering how
quickly you heal,
I wasn't especially
worried about it.
Some friends you are.
Look, you started it,
so don't complain.
[ARMIN] Plus, it's good
to see you feisty again.
I'm glad we met
with the commandant.
I think it helped.
I don't know about being feisty,
but I'll do what I have to.
And honestly, I feel better.
I just kept thinking about all
the stuff I couldn't change.
Spent so much time
pitying myself,
wondering why I couldn't be
strong like Mikasa and Levi.
I was jealous, but even
though you guys are strong,
you can't do all
that much alone.
None of us can.
That's why we have to
find our own roles.
When we join together,
that's when we become
truly powerful.
Everyone's got their
own strengths,
and it's 'cause of
times like this.
[ARMIN]
Yeah.
I think you're right.
Once we've retaken Wall Maria
and defeated every last
one of our enemies...
...can we go back?
To how things used to be?
[EREN]
Some things will be the same,
but some things have
changed forever.
And we'll make them
pay for that.
Yeah.
There's more out there, though.
The sea. Remember?
A body of water so big
that merchants could
spend their whole lives
and still not get
all the salt out.
There's so much beyond
the walls. Not just Titans.
Water that glows like
fire, fields of ice,
giant rocks that
take days to climb.
I joined the Scouts
so I could see all
those things someday.
Yeah. You sure did.
I remember.
[ARMIN]
All right then!
Let's start by finding the sea!
I can tell you still don't
think it's real, Eren.
You'll see! It does exist!
Heh. Okay, fine.
I guess we'll just have
to check it out, then.
[ARMIN]
That's not good enough!
You have to promise!
Oh, great, here we go again.
[ARMIN] This is our chance to
explore the outside world!
It's gotta be way bigger
than inside the walls!
Okay, I promise.
[EREN]
Just before sunset.
It's finally time.
[FLEGEL]
Hey!
Hange! Good luck!
[HANGE]
Flegel?
[CROWD cheering]
[CITIZEN 49A] Go out there and
take back Wall Maria for us!
The future of mankind
is up to you!
Captain Levi!
Good luck out there!
Thanks for saving our city!
[CITIZEN 49B] You guys come
back in one piece, all right?
[CITIZEN 49C] Yeah! But get
us back our land, too!
Someone's got a big mouth.
Yeah, well, that celebration
did get a little rowdy.
Actually, we ordered
all of that meat
from the Reeves Company, so...
Flegel.
[JEAN, CONNY, SASHA]
Yeah! You can count on us!
[CLARK]
I wonder how long it's been
since the Scouts got
a send-off like this.
I dunno. I'm not sure
if we ever have.
Well, as far as
I'm aware, at least,
this is a first.
[ERWIN yells]
[CROWD yells]
[yelling]
[CROWD yelling]
The operation to retake
Wall Maria begins now!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Scouts, move out!
♪ Closing Song ♪
You two.
[LEVI]
Do you have even the
faintest damn clue...
...what you're doing?
[gasps]
[MIKASA screams]