[HITCH] Don't'cha think
they have us spread out
a little too much?
We're more likely
to find them if we're not
all in the same area.
But why'd I have to get paired
up with you of all people?
Spill it, Marlo.
You scheme this up so
we'd get some alone time?
Look, Hitch. No offense,
but you weren't
my first choice either.
Oh, is that right?
Well, good for you then.
[MARLO] Anyway, doesn't
this seem odd to you?
Why would the Scouts
murder a civilian
and run for the hills?
This is the same group
of soldiers who consistently
risk their lives
for the sake of humanity.
Give me a break. Did you forget?
Think about what
they did to Stohess.
The way they turned it
into a battlefield.
How many dead bodies
do you think we carried?
Annie's been missing ever since.
They still haven't taken
her junk out of my room.
It's annoying.
[MARLO] But in doing so,
the Scouts also uncovered
a Titan in hiding,
and took it prisoner.
I highly doubt that the Military
Police could've done that.
How is disbanding the Scouts
what's best for humanity?
[gasps]
Be quiet.
Listen closely.
[water whooshing]
[MARLO]
Don't move!
Turn around slowly.
You must be a Scout.
Not a sound. Don't say a word.
Now listen, and do exactly
as I instruct you to--
[LEVI]
That's the way.
Now hand your guns
to the one in front.
Don't say a word, right?
♪ Opening Song ♪
[keys jingle]
[clang]
Sorry to have
kept you waiting, Erwin.
[door clangs, lock clicks]
I know this is sudden, but it's
time for your interrogation.
[ROY] So, the Survey Corps
murdered a civilian
in cold blood?
You're sure about this?
[NILE sighs] I'm told
that the evidence is strong.
But with that said,
I can't confirm anything
I haven't seen.
So then, the Interior Police
are running this case
--without oversight--
--Hey, you cut that out!
I'm sorry about him,
Commander Dawk.
Peaure here is still
just a rookie.
He doesn't quite understand
how things work yet.
Don't worry, the Interior
Police aren't a subject
we plan to write about.
And the same goes
for their new ODM gear.
Thanks Roy. See ya.
[NILE]
That new ODM gear worries me.
Those guns are useless
against Titans,
but they're perfect
for human combat.
It's as if that gear were
specifically made
for killing Scouts.
Also, judging from the fact
that its existence
was hidden from us MPs,
I get the impression
that we aren't off the list of
people it could be used against.
Anyway. We should get
a report from them soon.
Just be patient.
[FLEGEL panting]
[ROGER]
What's the rush, fat-ass?
Uh!
[ROGER] Way to go!
That's a dead-end, idiot!
[FLEGEL]
Dammit!
[FLEGEL gasps, yells muffled]
Shit, he disappeared!
Say what? Check the next alley!
He can't escape!
[HANGE] You're the son
of Dimo Reeves, right?
What's your name?
I'm Flegel.
Flegel. Nice to meet you.
My name's Zoë Hange.
This is sudden,
but if the MPs are trying
to hunt you down,
then I'm assuming that
you must know the truth
about your father's death.
Could you tell me
how it happened?
I made us stop
so that I could piss.
That's when the
Interior Police found my dad.
There was a tall guy
with a black coat and hat.
He slit my dad's throat.
Anyway, I'm glad to see
that you survived.
Now we can make
the truth known publicly.
You're crazy! Haven't you
seen today's newspaper?
If the MPs say you guys did it,
well, then that's the truth.
My testimony means jack shit!
They figured out I was there.
The Interior Police
know I saw everything.
I'll be hunted
for the rest of my life.
And all I can do about it is
run and hide until I'm caught.
My life is over now.
Shit!
Yeah. Maybe.
Thing is, that doesn't exactly
sound like living to me.
Try looking at it this way.
Instead of spending
the rest of your life
skulking around like a scared
rat till you get murdered,
you could stand up
like a human.
And face your enemy
even if they might kill you.
Why the hell would I?
Not everyone has
the same disregard
for their lives as you!
Know what? Yeah, I am scared,
and I have every right to be.
Your family. The company.
Don't you think they
deserve to know the truth?
Come on! That's just
what would be best for you!
[HANGE]
Of course it is!
You need to start thinking
about what's best for you, too!
[OLD CIVILIAN 41A] Hey! Who's
making a racket over my roof?
All right, you're comin'
with me, Flegel.
What? You're gang's
already lost-- just give up!
Why don't you know
when you're beat?
That's real simple.
Defeat is the only thing
the Scout Regiment
has ever known!
[LEVI] Get past the
checkpoint disguised as MPs.
Then snoop around until
we find out where Eren is.
It's a shit plan,
but it's all we have.
There's no time.
If we don't act now,
we're finished.
[JEAN]
Captain.
[LEVI]
Hm?
Now then. You're Stohess
District Military Police.
Private Marlo Freudenberg.
[MARLO] Captain Levi!
It's really him!
[LEVI] Same assignment,
Private Hitch Dreyse.
We'll need to dispose of you.
[HITCH, MARLO gasp]
Because of what you did,
Stohess was a graveyard.
Over a hundred people
were killed!
Huh?
--Hey!
--You bastards.
I bet you all think
you're some kind of
heroes of justice,
but you're not.
You dropped dozens of innocent
families straight into hell
on that mission of yours!
Yeah. We did.
Hey, you. You're from
the Southern Cadet Corps, right?
So you trained
with Annie Leonhart.
Were you a friend of hers?
[gasps]
[HITCH] No. She wouldn't have
made friends there, either.
Way too gloomy and
unapproachable for that.
She was just afraid of people,
like a scared little kid.
Now I'll never get the chance
to learn anything about her.
She's officially listed
as missing--you know why?
It's because one of your
Titans turned her into
an ugly red stain on the street!
Actually. No, it's because
the Titan we captured
was Annie Leonhart herself.
[BOTH gasp]
Goddammit. It makes me sick.
Nobody knows a thing
about this world.
Not us or anyone else.
Except for the bastards
at the center of it all.
We're letting you go,
but we need to give ourselves
a head start on you.
Annie.
Hey! Captain Levi!
Please, let me join
in your cause!
I believe that the Military
Police are in the wrong here.
If there's any way that I can
fight this world's injustice,
then that's what I want to do!
Easy. Calm down.
I swear, I won't
let you down, sir!
No. I have no way of telling
if you have enough resolve
to make an enemy of the state.
Let's go. Take them
deeper into the woods
and tie them up, Sasha.
[SASHA]
Sir!
Hey, Captain.
Would you let me do it instead?
[LEVI]
Knock yourself out.
All right.
[MARLO] We'll forget
everything we saw here.
I know ya will. Because both
of you are about to die!
Ah! No! He said to let us go!
The captain might be
a big softie, but I'm not.
I'm ready to do
what needs to be done.
You have to believe us!
We won't betray you--
we know that you're fighting
to protect humanity!
Right? Tell him!
As if I'd take your word for it.
I can't trust you--
not with that hair.
Who in their right mind
would get a bowl cut on purpose?
So how can I trust
a single word you say?
--[HITCH, MARLO yell]
--[JEAN] Uh!
[MARLO]
Run, Hitch. I'll cover you!
[HITCH screams]
What do you think'll
kill faster?
That knife,
or the gun at your chin?
Feel like tryin' your luck?
C'mon, let's race!
Please. We're on
the same side here!
Why the hell
would anyone believe
you wanna join the Scouts?
My comrades are getting rounded
up like criminals as we speak--
What makes you think we can win?
Because. You haven't quit.
Despite the odds,
the Scouts are still fighting.
I made a mistake when
I chose my regiment.
But you're a Scout.
You chose to risk
your lives for others.
So I'll trust you.
--[HITCH yells]
--[JEAN groans]
What the--?
Horse-faced jerk!
[MARLO] Stop! He was
just trying to test us!
[HITCH gasps]
[HITCH]
Huh?
Are you crazy?
Even with my hands bound,
I could've taken a swing
at you with that knife
and done some real damage.
How did you know
I wouldn't do it?
Don't ask me how, but you
remind me of this annoying guy.
An idiot.
Makes me wonder.
Is he one of the fools
Annie told me about?
Couldn't say.
All of us are fools.
[JEAN] Luckily for me,
you're just as dumb.
Marlo, I think you
proved your dedication.
[gasps]
This should be enough
to convince Captain Levi.
We'll be counting on you
from here on out.
[MARLO]
Far as I know,
this is the least-manned
checkpoint in the region.
Good. We'll handle
things from here.
Get back to your squad
before they're suspicious.
[HITCH, MARLO]
Right.
[LEVI]
Marlo, Hitch.
We're grateful.
[MARLO, HITCH]
Sir!
All right. This time
we're picking the fight.
[SOLDIER 41C]
Hm?
[SASHA, JEAN, CONNY yelling]
[thud]
[SOLDIER 41E, SOLDIER 41F groan]
[SOLDIERS groaning]
Stand down.
[SOLDIER 41C groans]
Captain. Isn't he--?
[LEVI]
He's with the Interior Police.
I've got questions for him.
Let's move.
[FLEGEL panting]
[ALL chuckling]
[ROGER] Thanks, dumbass.
There won't be any witnesses
in an abandoned dump like this.
Damn it!
I owe you big time.
Thanks a bunch, Flegel.
I mean, when you
gave us the slip before--
back in that alley--
I really thought I was screwed!
[sobbing]
My boss would've
killed me. I'm serious.
[chuckles]
Thanks for comin' back,
Flegel. Nice knowin' ya.
No! Wait.
Don't shoot yet, please!
Why did my father have to die?
Did the Interior Police
kill him?
What? I don't see
how that matters to you.
After all, you're about to be
a corpse yourself in a moment.
Please! Before I die,
I wanna know.
What did my father do
for you to justify killing him?
Huh? I thought you'd know.
He betrayed us
and started helping out
those bastards
in the Scout Regiment.
So his orders--they came
from the Interior Police?
You guys had him
kidnap those Scouts?
Well, it was a
different squad, but yeah.
Guess old Dimo didn't say
too much about it.
At least not to his
dimwit excuse for a son.
[FLEGEL] And what if
he'd refused to do it?
[ROGER]
Oh, he knew way too much.
We'd've killed him. I mean,
we killed him anyway,
but that's what he gets.
The damn idiot.
What made him think
the Survey Corps
could help this trash city?
[FLEGEL sighs]
You would never understand.
[ROGER]
Hmm?
You think you're real
smart shit, don't you?
Wanna know the last thing
my dad taught me?
He said a good merchant
should trust his nose.
And I'm glad I listened,
because it lead me to the people
who could avenge him.
And I side with them!
You're gonna die here, piggie!
No need to be brave--
go on and squeal!
My business with you
is over, asshole!
Why don't'cha
take a look above you?
[SOLDIER 41A, SOLDIER 41B groan]
[ROGER hollers]
--[HANGE grunts]
--[ROGER groans]
Ow!
Section Commander,
that was way too reckless!
We pulled it off!
Did everyone hear him?
No. The Scouts
are here? But why?
[gasps]
[CITIZEN 41A]
This "dump" ain't abandoned.
[CITIZEN 41B]
Bet it seems unlivable to you.
Yet we're here.
The place isn't half as nice
as it used to be,
but it's still our home.
We heard everything.
About Reiss.
And who had him killed.
Every last one of us
is a witness.
Yeah? Well, it doesn't matter.
'Cause it's the government
that decides what's true!
Idiots! Don't even think
for a second
you can get away with this!
You're in for a world of--
[groans]
Listen. You'll all be fine,
'cause The Reeves Company
will protect you.
You trusted my father, Dimo.
Well, now I'm in charge.
So, from now on
you can count on me.
That's a promise.
[CITIZENS clapping]
[CITIZEN 41A]
Glad to hear it, Mr. Reeves!
[CITIZEN 41B]
Speak up next time!
Glad to see you stepped up.
Hey. You give 'em hell, Flegel.
Right.
[HANGE]
Hm!
[clapping continues]
[SOLDIER 41C]
Screw you.
--[LEVI grunts]
--[squelch]
[SOLDIER 41C panting]
Where'd they take
Eren and Christa?
You bastards.
You think you're so brave.
That post was
manned by recruits.
They barely even knew how
to wipe their own asses.
No one's gonna think you're
heroes for beating them down.
Yeah, the guilt's
tearing me apart.
[SOLDIER 41C groans]
[LEVI] But what really gets
at me is this mouth of yours.
I'm gonna suggest
that you start talking
while you're still
able to use it.
Now, where are Eren and Christa?
[SOLDIER 41C gasps, coughs]
You can't win.
All that's left to you now
is to find some
filthy corner to hide in!
Covered in mud and shit!
If you don't turn yourselves in,
then every last Scout
we captured will get the noose!
Starting with the guiltiest
one of all, Erwin Smith!
--[groans, screams]
--[click]
Hurts, right?
That's what you get
for not answering my question.
Some Scout's lives are
more valuable than others.
Only those dumb enough
to agree to that join us.
Again, where'd they take
Eren and Christa?
I-I don't know.
Nobody told me, I swear!
Kenny Ackermann doesn't like
to make his business known!
Ackermann?
[MIKASA gasps]
I know Kenny.
That his last name?
[SOLDIER 41C]
It is, but--
He never was much of one
for sharing information.
Not important stuff, anyway.
But I bet you have
a rough idea.
You'd best try to remember.
No. Stop!
You still have plenty of
bones left for me to break.
Damn it. Are you insane?
Maybe.
Somebody's coming towards us!
And there's more than one.
Told you. You're beat.
Struggle all you want.
One way or another, the Survey
Corps will be destroyed.
[NILE]
You've seen better days.
Kinda funny. You were lecturing
me just the other day.
Soon, you'll be sent
before the king.
Then, his council will
determine your sentence,
and what to do
with the Survey Corps.
[ERWIN]
So you came.
[coughs]
Tell me Nile, where do you live?
Stohess, was it?
How's Marie?
How are your children?
I trust they're
all in good health.
Marie and the kids are--
They should be just fine.
I haven't been home in a while,
but it's in Wall Rose
on the east side.
I see.
Why ask that? What's going on?
[ERWIN] I entrusted something
to Commander Pyxis.
Whenever that
crucial moment comes,
what happens next
is out of my hands.
It'll be your choice to make.
Yours and theirs.
[DELTOFF] So, what did we learn
from the interrogation?
[GERALD] Not much. Erwin didn't
even realize that Pastor Nick
was with the Order of the Walls,
so Historia can make
all the claims about her name
she wants and it won't matter.
They'll all amount to nothing.
What a farce.
They don't know it, but in
truth they're nothing more
than cattle in a pen;
simply waiting to die.
--[knocking at door]
--[ALL] Hm?
My apologies.
But Erwin Smith has arrived.
[DELTOFF]
Very well. We'll be along.
Once Erwin has been executed,
all will be according to plan.
The secrets of the walls
will be kept as safe as ever.
And the king's peace
will be ensured.
Forever.
Erwin Smith.
Do you have any last words?
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR]
In order to protect the kingdom,
they kept the truth of the
walls--and the world--hidden.
But in doing so, they invited
an uprising of the people.
Next episode: "Reply."