♪ Opening Song ♪
Commander.
He's about to climb.
Soldiers!
You are not yet to engage
the Armored Titan!
Maintain a safe distance.
[SCOUTS]
Yes, sir!
[EREN]
Hange.
Why doesn't he have us attack?
What's he thinking?
[HANGE] The enemy prepared
quite the welcome.
He's watching their
movements for now.
Erwin doesn't want to act until
he understands their strategy.
[ERWIN grunts]
[ERWIN] That quadruped type has
some kind of cargo on its back,
which tells me that it
didn't transform just now.
[ERWIN] It's also likely that
this was the enemy's scout.
But for it to take
notice of our approach
and relay that
information to Reiner...
That must mean...
They have one more
intelligent Titan.
It's that quadruped type.
[LEVI, ARMIN gasp]
Though there may well be others.
[ARMIN]
That Titan is carrying cargo.
What could it be?
[BOTH gasp]
[roars]
Get ready!
Multiple two- to three-
meters approaching!
[ERWIN] This is just like
the siege of Utgard Castle.
They'll start by
targeting the horses.
Their primary objective
is still to capture Eren.
But towards that end,
they intend to eliminate
our only chance of escape.
[ERWIN]
As of five years ago,
Wall Maria's perimeter is
deep in Titan territory.
So, if they do
wipe out our horses,
we'll have no means
of getting back.
Not only would this
block our escape route,
it would cut off
our supply lines.
[ERWIN]
It might take a week or a month,
but there will come a point
at which none of us can move.
They'll forgo the risks
of a proper battle,
and opt instead to take Eren
once he's too weak to resist.
[ERWIN]
I'm sure of it now.
The proof is in the fact
that those larger Titans
are still standing in formation.
Their only purpose is
to prevent our retreat.
--[SCOUTS gasp]
--[ARMIN] Sir.
What now?
The Armored Titan is almost up!
Bertholdt hasn't shown yet,
but he must be nearby!
Yes. I'm well aware.
[ERWIN] At this point,
the thing I fear most
is that Reiner and Bertholdt
will reach our horses
and slaughter them unchecked.
Therefore...
You finally ready to
say something, Erwin?
Been waiting so long,
I could've made breakfast.
Dirk Squad and
Marlene Squad, too!
Join Klaus Squad and protect
the horses at the gate!
Levi Squad and Hange Squad!
I need you to take down
the Armored Titan.
Employ the Thunder Spears
at your own discretion.
Do whatever it takes to
achieve your objective!
This is our moment.
Our chance to strike.
The fate of humankind
depends on this battle!
Lay down your
hearts and lives...
...one final time, for humanity!
[SCOUTS]
Yes, sir!
[KLAUS]
Hear that?
We'll turn the tables
on the Titans
as they come for our horses!
[SCOUTS]
Sir!
Hey. Hold on, you two.
Hange can lead both your squads.
I'm going to need you
right here, Levi.
So I'll protect the
horses instead of Eren?
That's right.
And when the chance arises,
you'll strike him down.
You're the only
soldier I can trust
to dispatch the Beast Titan.
Understood, sir.
I wasn't fast enough to finish
off the Armored one earlier,
but I'll atone for that by
taking the Beast Titan's head.
[LEVI grunts]
[ERWIN]
Armin.
I have a plan for
the Armored Titan, too.
[ARMIN]
Uh--sir.
We have to win on two
fronts to secure victory.
I can handle one.
The other, I'll leave
to you and Hange.
[REINER]
There they are.
Gathered up in one place.
I'll kill the horses
and make a break for it.
That's good enough.
No matter how strong
Captain Levi is,
he's still no match
for our War Chief.
[sighs]
[REINER]
That was a close one.
If I was any slower in
transferring my
consciousness to my body,
I'd've died instantly.
[REINER] How did they even think
to check inside the walls?
[REINER]
Armin.
Was it you?
[REINER]
It doesn't matter now.
Once this is done, our long
journey will reach its end.
[REINER gasps]
[REINER]
Erwin Smith.
Can't let him distract me.
I've got to kill those horses.
[REINER gasps]
[REINER]
Eren!
[REINER] Why would he show up
when he doesn't have to?
They should be painfully aware
that abducting him is
our main objective.
[growls]
[REINER]
What is he thinking?
[REINER] Will he run south
and climb over the wall?
As a Titan, he could circle
around and escape to Trost
without a horse.
[REINER]
Were that to happen,
we'd have no reason
to stay here and fight.
Even if we did manage to
annihilate the Scouts,
Eren mastered hardening
in two months.
We can't let him
back in the walls.
No way.
If he learns how to harness
the Coordinate's full power,
we're finished.
[REINER]
Hold on.
Something's off here.
If his goal really
was to escape,
he would've used ODM gear
to scale the south wall
and then transformed.
[REINER]
But instead he transformed
right in front of me,
in the center of town.
[REINER]
I get it.
He's a diversion.
They're trying to change my
target from the horses to Eren!
You're not giving me any
time to think, Commander.
You clever bastard.
Makin' me get down
when I just climbed up.
[EREN]
Good. He went for it!
[HANGE]
He wants to use Eren as bait?
Yes, that was the
Commander's order.
[HANGE]
Hold on.
So he's willing to
risk Eren's capture
just to protect the horses?
You're kidding.
Even if we try it, Reiner might
just go after the horses anyway.
[HANGE]
No.
I'm sure he'll chase Eren.
If Reiner does go
after the horses,
then Eren can
continue running north
and wrap around the
Beast Titan's formation.
With Levi, the Scouts, and Eren,
they can catch the Beast
Titan in a pincer attack.
Erwin must've said as
much himself, right?
[ARMIN]
Um, yes.
Even if things
don't go as we hope,
the enemy doesn't
expect Eren to flee,
so it might confuse them enough
to get them to break ranks.
The only question is can
Reiner see that far ahead.
Knowing him, he should
work it out pretty quickly.
Okay.
This is where we'll bring
down the Armored Titan.
[ARMIN gasps]
Wait a second!
There's one more factor
we need to consider.
He's still hiding,
but Bertholdt must be nearby.
The last time they fought,
Eren outmaneuvered Reiner and
had him on the verge of defeat,
but then Bertholdt caught
him with a surprise attack,
and he ended up their captive.
[EREN sighs]
[ARMIN]
As a simple counter-measure,
do what you can to keep the
fight away from the walls.
[EREN]
It might've been a fluke,
but I've beaten you once before.
[EREN]
And I'm stronger now.
One-on-one, I can win.
[EREN] When it comes to
hand-to-hand combat,
Annie makes you look
downright weak.
[REINER TITAN grunts]
[EREN TITAN grunts]
[EREN] Do you have any idea
where we're standing right now?
[EREN]
This place...
[REINER TITAN groans]
[EREN]
...was my home.
Was our home!
--[EREN] But then you stole it!
--[roaring]
[EREN]
We're taking it back.
And you can't stop us.
[EREN] Get in our way,
and we'll slaughter you all.
[SCOUT 51A] Recruits!
Keep moving with the horses!
[SCOUT 51B] We'll keep
the Titans off your backs!
--[FLOCH] Hey, Marlo!
--Huh?
[FLOCH]
Where do we tie the horses?
We were told to avoid putting
all of them in the same place.
Just keep going, all right?
[SCOUT 51C] Two more small
ones coming from the east!
So those... are Titans?
[LEVI grunts]
[LEVI grunts, pants]
It's Captain Levi!
Now's our chance! Hurry!
Finish killing the
small ones already!
Get it done before
the Beast Titan moves!
And no casualties!
Don't you dare get eaten.
[SCOUTS]
Sir!
[panting]
[LEVI]
Shit.
Who the hell am I kidding?
These kids are gonna
drop like flies.
Shoulda left 'em up there.
[ERWIN] We struggle against
the smallest Titans now.
The Scouts have grown weak.
Most of our veterans have
been buried, burned, or...
[ERWIN] Still, if not for
the lives we sacrificed,
we never would have
made it half this far.
[ERWIN]
When I was a cadet,
I told the others about
my father's theory--
My faith in it.
I told them that
once I was a scout,
I would prove he was right.
[ERWIN] But once I actually
joined the Scouts,
I stopped talking
about it for some reason.
No, that's wrong.
[ERWIN]
It wasn't "some reason."
I'd realized something.
That of all my brave comrades,
only one was
fighting for himself.
They bled and died
for each other,
while I fought for
a selfish dream.
[ERWIN]
Then I came to lead my comrades.
Gave them orders
and inspiring words.
Be brave.
Give your hearts to humanity.
I played them all for fools.
Myself, too.
[ERWIN]
And now,
standing on this mountain
of brave corpses...
[ERWIN]
...I have quite the view.
Still,
Grisha's secret lingers
in the back of my mind.
Even if this plan should fail,
there's a chance that I could
still reach that cellar.
[ERWIN] Before I die,
I'd like to see it.
The truth of our world.
[yelling]
[EREN TITAN yelling]
[REINER TITAN grunts]
[EREN]
Those experiments paid off!
[EREN TITAN grunting]
[EREN] These fists are
all I need to beat you!
[EREN TITAN roars]
[REINER TITAN groans]
[EREN] When I focus my hardening
on one point, it gets stronger.
Since his armor's spread
across his whole body,
I can smash it like thin ice!
[REINER TITAN growls, grunts]
You're too slow, you stupid oaf.
You won't win!
[REINER TITAN grunts]
[EREN]
Damn it, no!
[REINER TITAN roars]
[REINER TITAN growls]
[REINER TITAN grunts]
[roaring]
[MIKASA gasps]
He needs our help!
[HANGE]
Not yet!
Everything rides on
our first attack!
We need to wait and trust Eren
to give us a good opening.
[REINER TITAN growling]
[EREN grunting]
[EREN] Your new weapon
is a big metal rod?
It's pointy, dumbass.
That makes it a spear.
The Corps of Engineers
really came through
for me with this one.
They've been going through
a plethora of technologies
kept hidden by
the Interior Police.
And I told 'em that
while they were at it,
they should try to
cook up a weapon
that'll work against
the Armored Titan.
And that's what
they came up with?
Our blades may as well
have been made of paper
against that armor of his.
All we could do
in our last battle
was watch Eren fight
the Armored Titan
from the sidelines.
There just aren't enough
openings in the plating
for us to cut through.
True enough.
Even at close range,
we couldn't do anything
to make him let Eren go.
[CONNY] Back then,
if the Commander hadn't
drawn that horde of
Titans towards him...
[HANGE] Until now, the only
attacks that've hurt Reiner
did so by working
around his armor.
I'm referring to Eren's
grappling techniques.
Also, Eren's been experimenting
with a new "hardened punch,"
for which we have high hopes.
With that said, if those
were our sole weapons,
this mission would
be doomed to fail.
It's vital that we plug
the holes in Wall Maria,
but what matters most here
is that we eliminate
Bertholdt and Reiner,
ensuring that they can't
breach the wall again.
Okay, so what's the plan?
We'll stab the Armored Titan
with those spears?
Think I'll just show you.
Let's go outside.
[thud]
[ALL gasping]
It's powerful, as you can see.
Not far from a lightning strike.
Hence our calling them
"Thunder Spears."
They're good weapons,
but are they enough to
bring down the Armored Titan?
There's no way to be
sure until we try.
These can tear
a normal Titan apart,
but to do real damage
against the Armored Titan,
it'll take some extra work.
[BOTH grunting]
[yells]
[REINER grunting]
[REINER]
Shit!
[REINER] It doesn't look like
biting Eren out of there
is something I can
handle by myself.
[REINER]
Guess it's on to Plan B.
[growls]
[HANGE grunts]
[HANGE]
Go! Now!
[gasps]
[REINER]
They're making a move?
I knew they've been gradually
surrounding me, but...
...how exactly do they
plan to hurt me?
I've got hardened plate armor
covering every vital
point of my body.
Their blades can't
even scratch it.
[MIKASA grunts]
[HANGE grunts]
[REINER gasps]
[roars]
[ALL gasp]
[EREN]
Did we do it?
[HANGE]
This just might work.
The Thunder Spears
are so destructive,
they pose a danger to
those who fire them.
If you anchor to
the Titan itself
and move in as if to
slash it with your blade,
you'll end up caught in
the resulting explosion.
Which means the only chance
to use Thunder Spears
is when the target is surrounded
by multiple tall,
solid structures.
We can only attack
with Thunder Spears
in situations exactly like this.
--[REINER TITAN groaning]
--[HANGE] Right here and now,
[HANGE]
we have to end it!
[SASHA grunts]
[ALL grunt]
[REINER gasps]
[CONNY yelps]
Good! We've got him!
The spears worked!
The armor on his nape
is in splinters now!
[CONNY grunts]
Whoa, it really worked?
We can actually do some damage!
[HANGE]
Do it again!
You each still have
a Thunder Spear.
Use them to end this!
[CONNY, SASHA gasp]
But it's Reiner...
Come on, guys!
We said we'd do it
if it ever came down to this!
So let's go!
[CONNY, SASHA, JEAN yelling]
[ALL grunting]
[REINER groans]
[REINER]
No! I don't wanna die!
[roaring]
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] If someone had
just said the right thing,
could the future
have been different?
Lives in the balance,
weighing them down.
None can be saved,
except through more death.
Next episode: "Descent."