♪ Opening Song ♪
Hey!
You get back here!
[KIDS laughing]
[JEAN]
Nice "palace."
[CHRISTA]
Don't you run from me!
[ARMIN]
Yeah, she's not exactly regal.
Well, it's only been two
months since she was crowned.
But it seems like she'd
rather run an orphanage
than a kingdom.
Have you heard the new name
the people came up with for her?
They call her the
Cattle-Farming Goddess.
I think it's a term
of endearment.
It's hardly the first time
she's been called goddess.
You know, if this keeps up,
I bet everyone'll forget
all about the chump
who plugged up
the wall in Trost.
This is part of why Historia
agreed to become Queen
in the first place.
So she could do all this.
Do what?
[EREN]
She went from the underground
to the edge of the walls
and saved all the orphans
and needy she could find.
She even got the
captain into it,
since he grew up underground.
When she sees someone crying
and saying that
no one needs them,
she has to prove them wrong.
She told me that she
needs them to be okay.
Slacking off again, huh?
[ARMIN]
Uh...
It's getting dark, you know!
Power changed her.
She reminds me of my mother now.
Gods can be cruel.
[CHRISTA]
So you're practicing hardening.
I hear it's going well.
It is.
But we need to hurry.
Before they come back.
What would you do?
If you found Reiner
and Bertholdt
and had to face them again?
I guess I'd have to
kill them. No choice.
[CHRISTA]
I hope we find out soon.
About this world and
how it became like this.
After all that we've done,
I don't wanna end
up with any regrets.
[KIDS laughing]
[CHRISTA] Even the kids
from the underground
have been smiling lately.
I refuse to think that
this was the wrong choice.
Yeah. You're doing
good things here.
I wasn't--
Which is funny,
considering how you said
that humanity should
get wiped out.
Oh, come on!
I got carried away!
What is it?
[MIKASA]
Gimme those.
[EREN]
Hey!
You need to rest
between experiments.
[CHRISTA]
That's true. Sorry, Mikasa.
[EREN] Hey, stop treating me
like a feeble old man, will ya?
[ARMIN]
As part of the coup de tat,
the military had to purge
people of considerable talent
from its ranks.
But discoveries such
as the glowing ore
in the underground cavern
counteracted these losses.
Also, thanks to Eren's
hardening ability,
a powerful new anti-Titan
weapon was invented.
[SOLDIER 48A]
That's it.
Jam your big head in here.
Do it now!
[HANGE]
Ooh!
That hit right at the
nape of its neck!
This could be it!
[BOTH gasp]
We did it! That's a
12-meter we crushed!
It worked.
Hell yeah!
With this baby,
we can kill Titans
without putting any
soldiers at risk!
We'll hack down those
bastards all day and night!
Say hello to the
Executioner from Hell!
We did it, Eren!
Eren?
It looks like he must've
overused his Titan abilities.
He's been doing hardening
experiments for days.
I'm sorry, Eren.
No, there's nothing
to apologize for.
We can't slow down just
'cause we're tired, right?
I'm fine.
Let's just make these
weapons quickly,
and then go to Shiganshina.
That's great! We can win!
With weapons like that,
killing Titans'll be
easy as breathing!
You're so damn excitable.
You should know better
than to be this pumped
about joining the scouts.
That reminds me.
Didn't Hitch try to
convince you to stay an MP?
Wait, Hitch? How come?
Because she's a thirsty girl,
and she thinks you're
a tall glass of water.
Can't say I follow,
but Hitch did tell
me off before,
saying I wasn't cut out
to be a real soldier.
She told me I should
"stop acting cool"
and just coast along in life.
I had thought she
was better than that.
So I told her I was
wrong about her.
Asshole.
[ARMIN]
Are you that dumb, Marlo?
No brain under that bowl cut.
[EREN] Calm down. He
didn't say anything wrong.
Well, anyway,
you should notice that the
only people as excited as you
are the new recruits with
no real battle experience.
Gimme a break.
Ya think you're some kinda
hardened veteran now?
I know I am,
compared to you at least.
[FLOCH]
That's rude.
We were in the 104th,
same as you.
N' besides, we're not
the only ones excited.
Everyone in the walls is.
We're taking Wall Maria back!
We're finally winning!
You think so?
Well, you guys do seem
a little different now.
There's something
about your faces.
What exactly happened?
Wanna know?
No. I'll ask some other time.
[CONNY]
I'm out. See ya later.
Huh? Now?
Tomorrow's s'posed
to be a prep day,
so I'm planning to head to
my village in the morning.
There's a chance I might
find somethin' new there.
Good night.
Think we could turn Conny's Mom
back to normal someday?
I mean, it's not
impossible, is it?
Well, if our knowledge about
Titans continues to improve,
then yeah, maybe.
[EREN] You're telling us
that Titans are people?
[LEVI] It's just a theory,
but it's possible.
[YMIR]
Oh, about 60 years.
Hell on earth.
Every day was like waking
up into a nightmare.
Like a nightmare.
[ARMIN]
Hm?
So much has happened that I
haven't had time to question it.
But who do you guys think that
it is we're fighting against?
The thing is, I've always
hated the Titans.
But what if they're just people
being tormented
by some nightmare?
For a time at least,
I was one of them myself.
Eren!
[gasps]
[MIKASA] You still have
bread and soup left.
You shouldn't be talking until
you've finished your meal.
Got it.
You're right. Sorry.
[JEAN]
Get it together, Eren.
Enough with the sad
mumbling, already.
It's all you do these days.
You know what you
should be focusing on?
That guy you saw.
From the memories
you were given,
when Reiss and
Historia touched you.
You said you saw a Scout that
must've known your dad, right?
Yeah.
I think he might've been with
my dad when the wall fell.
If he's alive,
he'll know something.
He seemed so familiar.
I can't shake the feeling
that I've met him somewhere.
Do you mean he seemed
familiar to you?
Or just your dad?
Me, I think.
It might help to smack
yourself in the head.
Yeah, you should try that out.
You know what else
might be helpful?
If instead of holdin'
hands with Historia,
ya got a head-butt
from the Commandant.
If that'd help me
remember, I'd--
Hey, wait.
[ALL gasp]
That's who I saw with my dad.
It's Commandant Sadies.
[HANGE]
Sadies was the 12th Commander
of the Scout Regiment.
And Commander
Erwin's predecessor.
It's been a long while
since I've seen him.
[EREN]
Commandant Sadies.
What's the matter,
Braus? Not gonna sit?
No! I'm quite fine
standing here, sir!
Let's see.
If I recall, back in the day,
I'd call you in here a lot,
when I was about
to chew you out.
It's only been a
handful of months.
And yet, I barely
recognize you kids.
So Commander Sadies--
Or wait, Commandant now.
We should be prepping
to recapture Wall Maria.
But tell me:
Why do you suppose we came
to speak with you instead?
Eren.
You look like your mother
in almost every way.
However, the daggers I
see within your eyes...
...those are your father's.
Tell me about him!
Tell me everything you know!
don't know much at all.
Not in the grand
scheme of things.
That said, I'll tell you a story
that's of no value
whatsoever to humanity.
The story of my past,
as nothing but a bystander.
[KEITH] Twenty years ago,
near Wall Maria,
I found him standing outside
of the gate to Shiganshina.
Hey, what are you doing?
How the hell did you get here?
Did you climb down
the wall somehow?
Wait, why would any of you
venture outside the walls?
Don't tell me you're trying
to fight those things.
[KEITH]
Huh?
Was it the truth or a lie?
He said he couldn't remember
why he was outside the walls.
All of his memories
had been lost.
Everything aside from his name.
Grisha Jaeger.
[HANNES]
Who knew it was a crime
to go into Titan territory
without permission?
I bet he's the first
guy who's tried it.
I mean, I always thought
that only you Scouts
were dumb enough
to go out there.
[KEITH] Something tells
me there's also a law
that jails idiots
who drink on duty.
Eh, Hannes?
Ugh. Anyway, it's not like
he actually hurt anybody.
So let's just keep it
to ourselves, yeah?
Yeah.
[KEITH]
So, Grisha.
Do you have any idea
where you'll go from here?
Maybe I can help.
There is one thing I remember
aside from my name.
I was a doctor.
Introduce me to a hospital.
I should be able to help there.
Huh.
[GRISHA] Also, do you
think you could teach me?
About this world, I mean.
And about the Scouts, too.
About everything
inside the walls.
[KEITH] He truly appeared
to know nothing at all.
Not about this world.
Not about anything.
I see.
Although there's inequality,
life in the walls is
largely peaceful.
And if nothing else,
you aren't living in
constant fear of the Titans.
That's good.
[KEITH]
You think so, do ya?
That means you're
just like the rest.
[GRISHA]
Huh?
We're trapped
inside these walls.
But as long as there's plenty of
food and alcohol to go around,
most people are
just fine with that.
In their whole lives,
they'll never question
how wide the world might be.
Is that why you risk your life
to venture outside the walls?
To see how wide the world is?
That's right.
Does it seem foolish?
No, quite the opposite.
The Scouts are wiser and
braver than anyone else
living within the walls.
Their very existence
is living proof
that the imagination and soul
of mankind are still free.
That's what you
think? Seriously?
Yes.
[CARLA]
What's this, Keith?
Huh?
You better not be recruiting
for the Scouts again.
No. Not this time,
Carla. I was just--
[GRISHA]
Oh, no.
I'm not really suited
for that kind of work.
It takes someone special
to become a Scout.
You have to be a chosen one.
That's one way to put it.
[KEITH]
I was a chosen one.
That was the first time
anyone had told me that.
But I knew that those walls
were far too cramped for me.
[KEITH yells]
So this expedition
failed as well.
[OFFICER 48B]
When will you finish the base
outside the wall?
[KEITH]
If only I was commander...
I could show results.
As idiotic as these people are,
I'd accomplish so much that
even they'd understand.
And then everyone would
have to acknowledge me.
[KEITH]
Grisha!
Carla caught the plague
that's going around.
They say there's no cure, but--
[GRISHA]
Put her in the rear bed.
Please, Dr. Jaeger.
My mom and dad,
they've gotten sick, too.
Not to worry.
I'll help everyone.
[HANNES]
Doctor! It's a miracle!
My wife is well again!
[CARLA]
Dr. Jaeger. Thank you so much!
[CITIZEN 48A]
Way to go! You'll do great!
[OFFICER 48A] You're hereby
appointed Commander
of the Scout Regiment.
[CITIZEN 48D]
Congratulations!
[applause]
[CITIZEN 48B]
Congratulations, Dr. Jaeger!
[SOLDIER 48C]
Shit! Our base!
[TITAN 48A roars]
It's no use! We need
to retreat! Commander!
[CITIZEN 48C]
The moron keeps leading his men
straight into death.
Yet he's the only one
who always lives.
[CITIZEN 48B]
That's not quite true.
I hear no one on Erwin's
squad has died yet.
[CITIZEN 48D] Then maybe
he should be Commander.
[KEITH]
Someone special.
A chosen one.
[CARLA]
Keith?
[gasps]
Carla. Who's the kid?
[CARLA]
Eren. Our baby boy.
I guess the news never
made it your way.
My husband worries about you.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Are you planning to keep this up
until you get yourself killed?
[gasps]
I think it's time.
Do you wanna know why
most people live and die
without accomplishing
a single damn thing?
It's because they've lost
their imaginations!
They'll complacently
waste their entire lives,
unashamed of the fact
that all they'll ever add
to the world is shit!
Such people are little
more than cattle!
They can't even
comprehend greatness!
Not even when it's right
in front of them!
So a girl who flirts
with every man in sight,
one who's good for
absolutely nothing
aside from keeping
people's drinks full...
...could never--
[KEITH]
It's true.
Normal people can't
accomplish a thing.
Hey, Erwin. I want you
to take my command.
[KEITH]
Special people do exist.
All this means... is that
I was never one of them.
It's such an obvious fact,
so why couldn't I see it?
[CITIZEN 48E]
Wall Maria has fallen!
Shiganshina District
was demolished!
They're gonna come
for Trost next!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[GRISHA]
Keith!
[KEITH gasps]
[KEITH]
Oh, yeah. That's why.
It's 'cause of what you said.
[GRISHA]
Eren.
Wake up, Eren.
Why wasn't your mother with you?
I'm sorry.
Mom was trapped,
and a Titan came.
[EREN]
It ate her.
[GRISHA]
Eren.
You'll avenge her. You must.
I know that you can.
Let's go.
Hold on. Where are you going?
[GRISHA]
Please don't follow us.
Grisha, why not avenge
Carla yourself?
I know you could do it.
All this time, you were
the one who was special.
I know that I never was.
But what if that boy
is the same as me?
What if he isn't a
chosen one either?
Is... Eren next?
Will you curse him too now?
This child isn't
like you, Keith.
Eren is my son.
Please don't get involved.
This is a family affair.
[KEITH]
That light.
After I found you,
I carried your unconscious body
back to the shelter... and left.
[KEITH]
And that is everything I know.
So that's it. I see.
At least now I know the real
reason you chose to resign.
Not to atone for all the
soldiers you got killed,
but because you realized that
you're not a special snowflake.
Just a delusional,
self-centered child.
Lay off him, Hange.
You had no right to keep
all of this to yourself,
just to spare your own ego.
We pledged to give our
lives and our hearts
for the good of mankind!
Please, let it go, Commander.
The Commandant was right.
Just like him,
I was never special.
Looks like... I was just
the son of a man who was.
That's all there is to it.
After I yelled at her, this is
what your mother said back.
Why should anyone
have to be special?
[gasps]
That just isn't the way
I like to look at things.
And when it comes to my child,
I don't care if he
grows up to be great.
My son doesn't have to
be better than anyone.
[CARLA]
After all, just look at him.
He's so cute.
I think Eren's special
enough already.
For no other reason than that
he was born into this world.
[KEITH] And you, just
like your father wanted...
...chose to set
your life ablaze,
and let it burn to ashes
outside the walls.
[KEITH] I tried, but in the
end, it all came to nothing.
I couldn't change a thing.
[KEITH]
I'm merely a bystander.
[NARRATOR] The night before
leaving for Shiganshina,
their sights set on the
world beyond the walls,
with hope and fear
in their hearts,
they pray for humanity's future.
Next episode: "Night of the
Battle to Retake the Wall."