[MAYAKA]
All right, then, Fuku.
Let me get this straight.
You mean this chocolate,
poured into a form,
cooled and hardened,
isn't homemade.
So you refuse to accept it.
Is that what you're telling me?
Yeah. That is what I'm saying.
[MAYAKA]
I see.
Okay, fine!
If that's how you really feel...
I won't forget about this!
Next year,
I'm going to shove a
masterpiece into your face
that's so amazing even you
won't be able to turn it down!
[MAYAKA] Making chocolate
from cocoa beans
is just too hard, isn't it?
[ERU]
Yes, it is difficult.
[MAYAKA] But I'm still
not going to give up!
I'll just have to make the
best dang homemade chocolate
anyone has ever had,
and if stupid Fuku
has any complaints,
I will chain him to a wall
and read every last word
of this book to him.
And if he still wants
to give me attitude,
I'll cram that chocolate
down his throat!
[ERU]
Mayaka...
I will help you!
[HOTARO]
What?
Ruthless.
If there's anything
I can do for you,
please let me know!
There is. Do you know
of any stores nearby
that sell fancy
baking ingredients?
Let me see.
There is a store by the market
that sells culinary supplies
for professional chefs.
Want me to show you where?
--[MAYAKA] Seriously?
--[ERU] Yes.
Hooray!
Promise that you
won't tell Fuku.
You have my word.
[HOTARO]
Have they forgotten I'm here?
[MAYAKA]
Okay, it's a date.
Oh, Oreki?
[HOTARO]
Hmm?
Don't you say anything, either.
Sure.
I mean it.
I won't say a word.
[HOTARO] And I'd appreciate
it if you'd stop giving me
that devil glare.
[HOTARO]
That's Satoshi's bike.
[SATOSHI]
Hey, Hotaro!
What a crazy coincidence,
running into you here like this.
So... Wanna play a game,
for old time's sake?
[HOTARO] I guess there's
no reason to hurry home.
[HOTARO] I haven't been
here since middle school.
[SATOSHI]
I hadn't, either.
I'll take the Viper Two.
You'll take the Raiden, right?
[HOTARO] It's the only
one I know how to use.
[GAME VOICE]
Airport. Get ready.
[HOTARO] I was sure he'd
focus on evasion tactics.
[HOTARO] Is this how
Satoshi usually fights?
[HOTARO]
No.
This is a definite change.
Satoshi's gaming
strategy when we were
in middle school was to
keep his eye on the prize.
[HOTARO] He would play
to win at all costs.
[SATOSHI chuckles]
[HOTARO]
And if that didn't work,
he was an awfully sore loser who
would throw tantrums and pout.
[SATOSHI] Let's switch
players and go again!
[HOTARO]
Is he trying to draw me in?
[SATOSHI]
Man! That sure was a good game!
Way to work that
joystick, buddy.
I mean it. That was fun.
[HOTARO]
Uh-huh.
Hey... toward the
end of the round,
why did you charge
in like you did?
When it comes to robot fights,
hand-to-hand is best.
It's more adventurous that way.
[HOTARO]
Yeah. This is the new Satoshi.
He's changed a lot
since middle school.
Man!
It does me no good
to tense up and overthink!
I'm certain that he'll
accept it this year.
I really hope you're
right about that.
By the way, Chi,
I've been wondering.
Who is your crush?
What?!
Well, um... I don't know.
Itchy.
[TOMOE] "This chocolate
is a gift for you
from your devoted older
sister, Tomoe Oreki,
trembling with what you
could call, 'sympathy.'"
Good morning, Oreki.
How are you?
Fine, thanks.
So how did Ibara's
chocolate experiment end up?
It's finished.
It turned out to be
quite a bit of work.
She had to sample all
kinds of chocolate.
I'll bet that was no problem.
She probably gobbled
all of it up.
[gasps]
That's not a nice thing to say!
[HOTARO]
Sorry.
But anyway,
because of that,
she was able to complete
her masterpiece.
I guess that's
what it looks like
to put your whole
heart into a project.
It's admirable.
[HOTARO] So, what's she gonna
do with the chocolate?
[ERU] Well, from what she
told me, it's complicated.
She couldn't manage
to get out of Manga Club.
I think she's just going to have
to leave it in the clubroom
or something. It's too bad.
[HOTARO]
Hmm...
I think Satoshi's
going to be thrilled
with the whole production.
[ERU]
Oh...
Hey, Oreki. Um...
Today is...
Well, it's Valentines' Day.
And in my family,
we don't traditionally
give anyone gifts
at the end of the year
or in the summer,
not in the way a lot
of other families do.
Also--not on Valentine's Day.
[HOTARO]
Does this mean...?
[ERU]
But still...
[HOTARO] So she's saying...
what, exactly?
[BOY 21A]
It's supposed to snow today.
[BOY 21B]
No way!
I didn't even bring any gloves.
I'm such a dummy.
Well, we're gonna be late!
Uh... yeah.
Shall we go, then?
Yeah. Sure.
[door opens, closes]
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro.
Hey, are you on your
way to the clubroom?
[HOTARO]
No, too cold in there.
I'm gonna wait in the
library till the sleet stops,
or turns to snow.
But you are, I take it?
Yeah. Sure am.
Apparently, Ibara's stuck in
Manga Club and can't come.
Word travels fast.
Chitanda, right?
Well, I'll see you later.
[HOTARO]
Satoshi.
Good luck to you.
What on Earth
would I need luck for?
[ERU]
Hey, Oreki.
Oh. Chitanda.
Do you have any
idea where Fukube is?
He didn't show up?
No. I thought something
arose unexpectedly.
[HOTARO] I saw him
a half an hour ago.
He was on his way
to the clubroom.
If you say so.
I'll wait for him
a little bit longer.
Fukube's late?
Something's off.
[ERU]
Oreki!
Please wait!
Something awful's happened!
It finally stopped sleeting,
and I was just about
to head on home.
Sorry, you'll have
to tell me tomorrow.
For real?
I'm sorry, but you
need to hear me out.
This is entirely my fault.
I carelessly left
the room unlocked.
And as a result...
Mayaka will be devastated.
[HOTARO]
Satoshi.
What happened?
Well... You see...
[ERU]
The chocolate...
Mayaka's labor of love...
...has been stolen!
[sighs]
All right.
I'll help you find it.
[ERU]
Okay.
[HOTARO] The last thing
I wanted was to be around
when Ibara got the news
that her chocolate was gone.
She worked so hard on it,
and I don't have much
of a stomach for horror.
Ah. Oreki, wait.
It doesn't look like we
can use the west stairs
to get to the fourth floor.
Then let's use the
east stairs instead.
Oh, excuse me a second.
Um... Does this look level?
It's kind of crooked.
Trapezoid?
It dropped too much.
What? Hmm...
How did that happen?
[ERU]
It was sitting right here!
Heart-shaped,
wrapped in plastic,
and about this big,
or maybe a bit bigger.
[HOTARO]
That's pretty big.
[ERU] It was sitting
right there on the table
when I left to go
look for Fukube.
Right, and when did you
get back to the clubroom?
Just after five.
I should have locked the door,
but I knew that I was
only going to be gone
for a few minutes.
Chitanda, there's no need to
beat yourself up about this.
It's completely my fault
for having been so late.
Have you mentioned
this to Ibara yet?
[ERU]
No, I haven't.
Call me a coward,
but I can't bring myself to
until I've done all
that I can to find it.
[HOTARO] And it's
definitely not in this room.
[ERU]
Right.
Fukube and I have scoured
every corner in here
and all around the building.
[HOTARO]
Satoshi, too?
[SATOSHI] I ran into her
coming down the stairs,
so we came up
and looked together.
Ah, that makes sense.
And the Industrial Arts guy?
How long was he there?
Wait, which guy?
[HOTARO]
The one with the poster.
[ERU] You mean the boy
with the glasses?
Well, he was already
on the stairs
messing with that thing
when I left the room
to look for Fukube.
[HOTARO]
Perfect.
If the Industrial Arts
kid was on the stairs
the whole time you were gone,
he would have seen
who came and left.
That's lucky!
Hold on.
Isn't it possible
that he did it?
That's not likely.
What kind of culprit lingers
near the scene of the crime,
casually hanging up
a poster like that?
Yeah, fair enough.
[INDUSTRIAL ARTS CLUB 21A]
People who've passed by here?
[ERU]
Yes.
Yeah, I remember.
There were only three.
Three people?
Well, what did they look like?!
Were there any
distinguishing characteristics?
One.
And two.
And three?
Mm-hmm.
[HOTARO] In other words, the
culprit is still lurking around
on the fourth floor.
Satoshi, what clubrooms
are located on this floor?
The Classic Lit Club,
Light Music Club,
Astronomy Club,
and the Philosophy Club.
But then...
Other than us, the Astronomy
Club is the only one
that hasn't gone home yet.
[SATOSHI]
I have to say, this is weird.
You're really getting
into this, huh.
It could start
sleeting again, you know.
Leave me alone.
We'll be able to find it,
won't we?
Even so, why would
anyone just steal like that?
[HOTARO]
That's a great question.
Why would they?
Why don't we start by exploring
all of the possibilities?
[knock on door]
[SAWAKIGUCHI]
Coming!
What? Classic Lit Club?
Kindly give us
back our chocolate!
Never mind her.
We just came to ask you
a question, that's all!
--Yeah? What?
--Well...
[HOTARO] It's just that someone
stole Valentine's chocolate
from our clubroom,
and we only came to ask
if you might have seen anything.
Huh?
Sounds like we've got
ourselves a love bandit!
Did you see anyone
suspicious up here
between around 4:45 and 5:00?
Umm...
We were pretty much already
in the swing of things here.
I don't know what time,
but Nakayama and
Yoshihara stepped out.
Oda might have left,
too, but again,
I don't know when they did.
[HOTARO]
Three out of five, huh?
Did anyone start to pack
up their things to go home?
No, nobody did.
So that girl in the group
over there, is that Oda?
That's Nakayama.
Just so you know, Detective,
nobody came in this room
with any stolen chocolate!
Hey, guys.
Did any of you catch
a whiff or a glance
of anything chocolatey?
Man, nobody here got
any Valentine's sweets.
You don't have to rub it in!
I really wish that I had!
Turned down again?
[laughing]
There you have it.
Anything else
you'd like to know?
No, that's it.
Thank you all for your time,
and I truly didn't
mean any disrespect.
Fine. I guess I forgive you.
[SAWAKIGUCHI]
Okay, let's get back to it!
[ODA] Too late,
you're out of the game!
She seemed annoyed.
Or did I imagine that?
Of course she was.
But we have to do
everything we can
to get Mayaka's chocolate back!
Hotaro...
[HOTARO] For now, I think we
should just go back
to the clubroom.
We'll plan our next step there.
[HOTARO] Is there any way
to get to the fourth floor
besides the stairway?
Unless you count climbing
the outside walls,
just the stairs that were
closed and being waxed,
but there was no sign
that they were used.
Okay.
Come to think of it, we didn't
check the girls' restroom.
[ERU]
I'll go check now!
Do you really think it
could be in the bathroom?
The odds are about
one in a million.
So you're saying
there's a chance?
Satoshi!
I have a good idea
of what happened.
Just keep your mouth shut.
Okay.
It wasn't in there, either.
Well, that leaves
one more option.
[MAYAKA]
Huh?
What are you guys
doing in here?
--Listen. Mayaka--[gasps]
--[MAYAKA] What did you think?
How was it?
My homemade chocolate?
[HOTARO]
She wasted no time.
--Ibara--
--I'm so sorry, Mayaka.
I left the room for a few
minutes to look for Fukube.
and someone stole the
chocolate while I was gone.
I feel terrible!
Really? So someone stole it?
Mayaka. I apologize.
Please don't feel bad.
You have no reason to
be sorry, Chi, seriously.
Although, it is unfortunate.
I'm going home now.
For real,
don't let it bother you.
Please step aside.
Where are you going?
I will find that
chocolate even if
I have to resort to
desperate measures.
If I don't, there's no way
I can show my sorry face
to Mayaka tomorrow.
[HOTARO] This isn't
your fault, you know.
You're wrong, and I
can't forgive myself
for what happened!
Today was supposed to be
a happy day for Mayaka.
She deserved that!
[HOTARO] I can't say I
identify with how you feel.
I'm not as sensitive
to others as you are.
But please just
let me handle this.
There are a few things
I need to check out,
and I can't do that
with you around.
Do you have a suspect?
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
Nakayama, from
the Astronomy Club.
[HOTARO] Ibara's chocolate was
a pretty decent size, right?
So it couldn't be hidden
under a guy's uniform.
You could try to conceal it,
but it would make your
movements awkward.
It would be easier with
the girls' sailor uniform.
If you strapped it to your leg,
the skirt would hide it easily.
I promise I'll get
Ibara's chocolate
to Satoshi by
the end of the day.
Let me take over from here.
You just go home and relax.
Okay, I will.
I'm trusting you
with this, Oreki.
Should we get going?
Sure.
[HOTARO] Satoshi. Let me
see your drawstring bag.
[HOTARO] I am now giving
Ibara's chocolate to you.
This fulfills the promise
I made to Chitanda.
[HOTARO] I did know
who took the chocolate.
It was Satoshi.
Excellent work, Hotaro.
[HOTARO] The moment I heard the
chocolate had been "stolen,"
I suspected that Satoshi had
taken it from the clubroom.
My suspicions were confirmed
when we talked to
the boy on the stairs.
Satoshi said,
"it dropped too much."
Unless he had told the kid to
drop it at some point earlier,
he wouldn't have
responded that way.
Satoshi probably waited
in the boy's restroom
on the third floor for
Chitanda to pass by.
Then he got the chocolate
from the clubroom.
But it was bigger
than he expected.
It wouldn't fit in his
bag in one piece,
and there wasn't
a large enough bag
anywhere in the room.
If he didn't hide it, and
happened to bump into Chitanda,
he'd have been caught.
Which meant his only
option was clear.
You didn't even think twice
about breaking it in half.
I guess this means we're even.
Even?
Yeah, last April.
You invented that story
about the Spider Society
so I could escape Chitanda.
Ah, you're right.
I had forgotten about that,
but no one was hurt
in the process there.
Except for you, that is.
Well, are you at least gonna
tell me exactly why you did it?
And don't even try to
say that it was just a joke.
What if it was?
[SATOSHI grunts]
Then I'd have to
teach you a lesson.
For Chitanda and Ibara.
By force.
Well, I don't
want to get beat up.
I'd rather not say. Still...
I guess I'm gonna have to tell
you one way or another.
Hotaro, be honest, now.
Do I strike you as
the compulsive type?
I think you fixate
on your interests.
That's where
you're wrong, though.
People like that will
actually apply themselves
and not let others beat them
when they are truly passionate
about what they do.
And you're different somehow?
I am.
I'm never going to be
the best at anything,
but to be more specific,
I've given up any chance of it.
I'm no longer trying
to be the best.
You sensed something had
changed at the arcade, right?
I wasn't the way I used to be?
I wasn't obsessed
with winning anymore?
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
[SATOSHI] The old me wanted to
win just for the sake of glory,
and I was a lot
fussier in general.
It stopped being fun
for me, you know?
Caring so much about the
prize took the joy out of it,
even when I did win.
I couldn't handle that.
If you don't have fun when you
win, what's the point of it all?
So one day I just
decided to let go.
I chose to be particular
about not being particular.
Once that changed,
I could enjoy life again.
I can have a good time now.
But there was one little
problem with my plan.
Mayaka.
Mayaka is awesome. Really.
There's truly
no one else like her,
and the fact that she likes
me and wants to be with me
is nothing short of
a dream come true.
What, then?
That's the rub.
How can that be okay?
To be so obsessed with her?
[SATOSHI] I want to be with her,
there's no question about that.
But I don't want
to fixate on her.
It's all about what I want.
I don't even consider
how Mayaka feels.
[chuckles] I know that
sounds self-centered,
but I don't want to take
Mayaka for granted, either.
Besides, if I let go
of my new philosophy
and give in to my
feelings for Mayaka,
I take the chance that I'll
revert back to my old ways.
I'm terrified by that prospect.
That's why you didn't
accept the chocolate?
Exactly. It's been a year.
And I still haven't figured
out a real solution.
This was the only
way I could try
to avoid accepting a gift
that I couldn't receive.
But you also hurt Chitanda
in the process.
Things don't work for me
the same way they do for you.
I didn't think about Chitanda
when I dreamt all this up.
[ERU]
Mayaka!
Please, wait a sec!
[MAYAKA]
Hey, Chi.
--[ERU] Look.
--[MAYAKA] I'm sorry!
I actually know who stole
the chocolate, already, okay?
What?
The truth is, last year,
I told Fuku I'd wait till this
Valentine's Day for his answer.
This whole thing
was just to test him.
Then the chocolate...?
[MAYAKA] I'm pretty sure that
he's the one who stole it.
Huh... That's what happened.
I feel really terrible that
you went to so much trouble.
I'm sorry I tricked you.
No.
I am the one who blew everything
way out of proportion
in the first place.
So...
That means when Oreki
said that the girl
from the Astronomy
Club stole it...
[MAYAKA]
I think that he was just telling
a white lie to cover for Fuku.
[ERU]
That makes sense.
But that's so mean of Fukube
to play along like
he didn't do it!
You think so, too?
I do!
It's just appalling!
But not as appalling
as me still liking Fuku
after everything
he has done to me!
That's it, Chi.
We deserve some cake right now!
We do!
[SATOSHI]
Well, Hotaro...
Now you've heard
everything that I have to say.
So?
This is probably not something
we should share with Chitanda.
No way.
I really don't
wanna get beat up.
That said...
What are you going to tell her?
When will you give
Ibara an answer?
[SATOSHI] I think my
answer will come very soon.
[HOTARO]
That's good.
[HOTARO] For all your
deftness, you're still clumsy.
[HOTARO] "Sorry. I now see I
don't know anything about you."
That's what I thought, but I
couldn't bring myself to say it.
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
I ended up getting the chocolate
back safely to Satoshi.
Did you really?
That's such a relief.
[HOTARO]
Good.
So don't give it
too much thought.
[ERU]
Oreki...
I want to thank you
for everything you did
to help today.
Sure.
[SATOSHI]
Hello, Mayaka? It's me.
Listen, I really need
to talk to you.
[HOTARO]
Bitter.
[HOTARO] Next time: "The Doll
That Took the Long Way Around."