[HOTARO shivering]
[HOTARO]
Hey, Chitanda.
Isn't there a superstition
that whatever you do
on New Year's Day, you'll
end up doing all year long?
[ERU]
Well, yeah. Maybe.
But that doesn't make much
sense, if you think about it.
Otherwise, it would
mean that if you took
New Year's Day off,
then you would be off
for the rest of the year,
which is completely ridiculous.
How could that ever happen?
[HOTARO]
Oh, right.
[ERU]
Anyway, Oreki... Not to be rude,
but right now I am a
little bit more concerned
about our current
predicament than I am
about the next 364 days.
[HOTARO sighs]
How did we end up in this state?
[ERU]
That's a good question.
I'd say it's mostly because you
picked an unlucky fortune,
wouldn't you?
[phone ringing]
[HOTARO]
Yes?
[ERU] Hello, this is
Eru Chitanda speaking.
Is that you, Oreki?
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
[ERU]
I was wondering...
Do you have any plans
for New Years' Day?
No plans so far.
[ERU]
Great!
Well, do you want to visit
the Arekusu Shrine that day?
[HOTARO]
Visit the shrine?
[ERU]
Yes.
Mayaka said she got a job
there over the holidays.
She's working as an attendant.
That's not really up her alley.
[ERU] That's not very
nice of you, Oreki.
Fukube said that
it sounds like fun
and that he'll be
joining us, as well.
And I was thinking...
[HOTARO] Thinking what?
Is there something else?
[ERU] It's not a big deal or
anything, I just had an idea.
I kind of feel like
wearing my kimono,
but I'm a little nervous.
[HOTARO]
Oh.
It's cold.
[HOTARO]
It's New Year's, all right.
I guess a lot of people like
to get dressed up for it.
Ah! Hello, Oreki!
Happy New Year.
I hope it brings you luck.
Oh...
Happy New Year and
luck to you, as well.
I'm excited to
continue our friendship.
May it grow throughout the year.
Oh, yes, may it continue
to flourish and prosper.
I wanted to show
off this outfit tonight!
Well, then. Shall we go in now?
Huh? Yeah.
[HOTARO]
Can I carry that?
[ERU]
Huh?
Yes, that would
be really helpful.
Thanks for offering.
[HOTARO]
What is it?
[ERU]
A bottle of saké.
My family does business
with the priests here,
so I wanted to bring them
a New Year's present
from my father.
[HOTARO] Running around bringing
New Year's gifts to priests?
Sounds like a hassle.
The real hassle was
running around all day today.
I spent all morning and
afternoon visiting relatives
and paying respects.
What were you up to today?
Anything interesting?
What did I do?
[HOTARO] I got in some
good practice on my
hermit crab impression.
[TV show music playing]
Hermit crab?
[HOTARO] Never mind,
it was a stupid joke.
Where's Satoshi?
I don't know.
Mayaka's the one who talked
to him about coming here
with us tonight.
Oh, you know what, Oreki?
Hmm?
Why don't we start
by offering our prayers?
[HOTARO]
Okay, I wanna get this right.
May I only expend a
moderate amount of energy
for this entire year.
Excuse us, is anyone here?
May I help you?
Hello, sir.
A very Happy New Year to you.
On behalf of Tetsugo Chitanda
and the rest of our family,
I've come to pay my respects.
I'm his daughter, Eru Chitanda.
Hotaro Oreki, tagging along.
Oh, so you're
Tetsugo's little girl?
Please, come in.
Make yourself at home.
I'll go and get Kaho.
Thanks, and pardon
the intrusion.
[HOTARO] So this is a
genuine shrine priestess?
Very distinguished.
Happy New Year.
I hope it brings you luck.
And I look forward to
happy relations with you
in the coming year, too.
Happy New Year.
May it bring you luck, as well.
I have brought a bottle of
saké as a gift from my father.
I do hope you will accept it.
[HOTARO] So this must be
how the other half lives.
Thank you for your generosity.
I accept this gift.
Well, uh...
It's nothing super fancy.
[ERU laughs]
Please, Oreki.
It's not your place to say that.
We don't want it
if it isn't fancy.
What?
Oh, don't scare him like that.
Please accept our gift.
Though it really
is nothing special.
[HOTARO]
They're messing with me,
and I freaked out like a dork.
You're in class 1-B,
isn't that right?
Yeah, I am.
[KAHO] I thought Fukube
was coming with you guys.
[HOTARO]
How does she know that?
Divine psychic powers?
This is Kaho Jumonji.
She's also in class 1-B.
You mean we're classmates?
[BOTH laugh]
We'd like to see Mayaka Ibara.
Do you know where she is?
Ibara? Oh, that girl.
This will take you right
to the back of the kiosks.
You can go on ahead.
[ERU]
Hey, Mayaka!
Oh. Chi, you made it!
[ERU] That hairstyle looks
really pretty on you!
[MAYAKA] That's 'cause
they did it for me!
Don't stare.
Happy New Year.
I hope that it brings you luck.
Happy New Year!
Look at your kimono!
It's so beautiful!
Thank you for saying so!
Is it long-sleeved?
No, it's the normal pattern.
I'm not allowed to wear
the ones with long sleeves
until I go to college.
I'll be getting out of here
in about an hour or so.
What are you guys gonna do?
I think we'll just stay
in the main hall area
and wait for you to get done.
Where is Fukube?
He was here earlier in the day.
He went home to watch
some drama on TV.
What was it called?
Dark Clouds: Odani Castle ?
I think that's it.
He should be back in
a little while, though.
So Ibara, what do they
have you selling in there?
Just fortunes.
I also give change,
and it's the lost and found
for kids and belongings.
The parishioners who volunteer
are a little overzealous,
so if anything at all gets
found, they bring it right here.
It was way busier earlier today.
Lost children everywhere.
[HOTARO] Don't remember
asking, but great.
A new year's fortune
sounds like fun.
I'll take one of those.
[MAYAKA]
Okay, pick one out, then!
Sure.
[MAYAKA]
Whoa, that purse is amazing!
I've never seen one
so fancy in real life!
[ERU]
Thanks, I'm glad you like it!
You're so darn happy.
Yep!
[MAYAKA]
Here you go.
I got number 10!
Here, Oreki, do you wanna play?
Uh-huh.
--Here.
--Thanks.
[ERU]
Wow! Great luck!
[MAYAKA]
That's awesome, Chi!
[ERU]
Yeah!
Number 16.
[ERU] Did you get
a good one too, Oreki?
[HOTARO]
Uh, nah, but it's fine.
I still think it's going
to be a really great year.
If you say so, sir.
I've never known anyone who got
a bad luck fortune
before tonight!
You're really that
excited by my bad luck?
I'm so sorry.
No, I'm not excited,
and I can understand
if it's bothering you.
Fine, gimme my curse.
[ERU]
Kaho!
Oh, I'm sorry, Eru.
I forgot to offer you tea.
[ERU]
No, never mind that.
Did something
happen around here?
One of the part-timers
knocked over some pots
and made a mess.
Now we have to whip up
a ton of dumpling soup
and sweet saké on
the fly for the guests.
Oh, that's terrible.
Was she burned?
[KAHO]
No, it missed her, thankfully.
I want to help you.
[KAHO]
Not so fast!
There's no way I'd let
you cook dressed like that!
Well, is there anything else
I can do to be of assistance?
Yeah, could you
bring in some saké lees
from the storehouse?
They're right to your left
when you walk in,
so you should be able
to recognize them.
So sorry.
It's fine!
I'll tag along and help you.
[HOTARO]
The storehouse...
I think I remember seeing
it by the Inari statue.
Whew, it's freezing.
Let's hurry up and
get this over with.
[HOTARO]
That's not very secure.
I really hope there's
a light in here, at least.
Me, too.
[HOTARO] There's nothing
but a wall to the left,
where she said.
You think that she could
have meant farther inside?
[ERU]
Yeah. That's possible.
[HOTARO] I thought this would
just be a quick errand,
but it's turning out
to be a pain.
[ERU]
Hey, Oreki.
This place...
It is a shed, right?
[HOTARO]
Yeah, I think so.
You could call it a shed
or maybe even a shack.
Is this really the right place?
[ERU]
No, the storehouse.
[HOTARO]
Huh?
[ERU]
This isn't it.
Kaho said to look
in the storehouse.
Oh, my family doesn't
have a storehouse,
so I just got confused!
[giggles]
[HOTARO]
I can't say that.
[HOTARO] When did you
plan on mentioning it?
[ERU] Sorry about that,
Oreki, it just dawned on me.
I remembered that the
mikoshi storage room
is right next to the
shrine office, though.
[HOTARO]
Then let's head over there.
[PARISHIONER 20B] Oh.
Someone left this unlocked.
I'll fix that!
[HOTARO]
Please say he didn't!
--[door rattles]
--[HOTARO grunts]
[ERU]
Hey, what's the matter?
[HOTARO]
We're locked in here.
Sorry.
This is all because
I made one stupid mistake.
[ERU] No. It's just as
much my fault as yours.
And anyway, it's not our
fault we got locked in.
[HOTARO sighs]
All right. Well...
I'm gonna yell for help.
I'm about to scream as loud
as I can, so cover your ears.
[ERU]
Hold on! Wait!
[HOTARO]
Ah... Ah...
[ERU] Please don't
draw attention to us!
[HOTARO gasps]
[ERU]
Ah! I'm very sorry.
It's just...
You can't yell for help.
[HOTARO]
'Kay?
[ERU]
Because...
If someone out there hears
and comes to let us out...
What will happen after that?
[HOTARO] Well, I imagine
they'd rush over,
unbar the door, and we'd be
free to finish what we started.
[ERU] But how would it look
when they opened the door
and found us together?
[HOTARO]
What do you mean?
[ERU] All of those
parishioners...
They know my family.
If they came to rescue us,
they would recognize me,
and if they saw us
in here together,
they would misunderstand!
I am only here tonight
to represent my father.
If it were another night,
it might be different,
but tonight would be
the worst possible time
for them to find us.
It would be a major scandal!
[HOTARO sighs]
[HOTARO] I guess I just
don't understand her world.
[HOTARO]
I hear that.
What do you propose we do?
If someone comes in to get
something and finds us alone,
not making a peep,
they're definitely gonna get
the wrong idea.
[ERU] The only people here who
wouldn't jump to conclusions
are Kaho and Mayaka.
[HOTARO]
True.
[ERU gasps]
Oh my gosh!
I just had the greatest idea!
[HOTARO]
Yeah?
[ERU]
Our cell phones!
We can just shoot them a
text and they'll let us out!
[HOTARO] I can't believe we
didn't think of that before.
Go ahead, then.
[ERU] I didn't bring
my phone with me.
We'll have to use yours.
[HOTARO]
I don't have one.
[ERU gasps]
That's terrible!
How are we going
to get out of here?
[HOTARO] Well, we can't
take the door off its hinges
from this side.
[ERU]
You know... Forget this.
I didn't know you didn't
have a cell phone,
and that's why I said
not to shout for help.
I thought we had options.
I just blanked for a few
minutes on who to call,
but when it dawned on me,
it didn't matter anymore.
[HOTARO]
Mm-hmm.
[ERU] But desperate times
call for desperate measures.
So go ahead and yell.
I'd rather risk my reputation
than risk either of us
catching a cold.
[HOTARO] But you wouldn't
be too happy about it
if they were to misunderstand.
Look, we'll only shout
out for help as a last resort.
Until then, let's brainstorm for
anything else we could try.
[ERU]
This is awful.
[HOTARO] We can't move
the bar, call out,
or take the door off its hinges,
but there are still
four avenues of escape
we haven't explored yet,
so don't give up.
[ERU]
What? There are that many?
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
One, we kick the door down.
Two, we tear down
one of the walls.
Three, we dig a tunnel to the
outside through the floor.
Four, we bust a hole
through the ceiling.
[ERU] No way!
We can't do any of that!
To you it may
just be an old shed,
but it's still one of
the Arekusu shrine's
sacred buildings!
[HOTARO]
Yeah, you're right. Silly me.
--[ERU gasps]
--[HOTARO] Huh?
[ERU] It looks like
someone's coming this way!
[ERU] It's a parishioner
volunteer making his rounds.
And from what I can tell,
it looks like he found
a cell phone strap.
[HOTARO]
You can see that?
[ERU] Really well.
I have great night vision.
[HOTARO]
What is she, a wild animal?
[ERU]
Oh, good, he's walking away.
He's going to drop it off
at the shrine office.
[HOTARO]
The shrine office.
[HOTARO] Listen, Chitanda,
do you think it'd be okay
to break open the wall
just a little?
[HOTARO] Ibara mentioned
earlier that any time someone
drops something of value,
the parishioners bring it over
to the shrine office.
Well, right now, Ibara is
in charge of lost items.
[ERU]
Right.
[HOTARO] So we can drop
something out there
that obviously
belongs to one of us.
When they bring it to her,
she would recognize it
and pay closer attention
to it than other things.
If we could somehow convey our
current predicament to her,
she would come let us out!
[ERU]
That might work!
[HOTARO] Whether or not she
makes the connection to the shed
is the hard part, so we'll
need all the luck we can get.
Let's just hope she gets it.
[ERU]
We could drop my handkerchief.
I'm pretty sure Mayaka has
seen me use it several times.
[HOTARO]
Perfect.
That's what we'll use, then.
[pounding noise]
[HOTARO] Okay, Chitanda,
drop your handkerchief
through the hole.
[ERU]
Oh. Right!
[HOTARO]
Please let this work.
Ah. Jumonji.
Happy New Year to ya!
Happy New Year to you, as well.
Hey, have you seen Eru,
by any chance?
[SATOSHI]
Chitanda?
I just got here, so I haven't
run into anyone yet.
[KAHO]
Oh.
Sorry I can't show you around,
but you can go in on your own.
The stove is on in the
great hall, if you're cold.
[SATOSHI] I always feel so
awkward around Jumonji.
[SATOSHI]
Mayaka!
Fuku, hey.
[SATOSHI] Is she still
embarrassed about her
attendant outfit?
It must be pretty hard
to work in the cold.
You're a real trooper.
[MAYAKA]
Mm-hmm.
But enough about me,
how was your show?
It was an absolute
masterpiece!
I couldn't have asked for
a better start to the year!
Really?
Oh, that's right.
Look, Fuku, does this
handkerchief look familiar?
Sure doesn't.
It looks a lot like
one that Chi has,
but I'm not really sure.
It's convenient
that you might know
who the owner is,
don't you think?
When you see Chitanda
in a little while,
you can ask her about it.
Oh, yeah.
You're right, I can!
[ERU]
We're done. Help isn't coming.
[HOTARO shivers]
I thought that our handkerchief
plan would work for sure,
but it seems that alone
isn't gonna cut it.
[ERU] I guess my hanky
didn't leave a strong
enough impression.
[HOTARO] All right!
Now it's time to execute plan B.
My wallet should do the trick.
[PARISHIONER 20B]
Here, found this, too.
[MAYAKA]
Thanks.
Hey, Fuku, look at this!
[SATOSHI] That's Hotaro's
wallet, isn't it?
Looks like that moron
must have dropped it.
And to make matters worse,
it's been emptied out, too.
[SATOSHI]
What's that?
[MAYAKA]
That's the fortune he drew.
Whoa!
[SATOSHI] Hotaro drew bad
luck and it came true.
But this is strange.
Except for that fortune,
his wallet's empty.
[SATOSHI]
Mayaka.
I want to draw one
of those fortunes, too.
Seems like yours might
be the real deal.
[HOTARO shivering]
[ERU]
Help isn't coming, is it?
[HOTARO]
No.
[ERU sneezes]
[HOTARO]
Are you feeling okay?
[ERU]
Yeah.
I'm regretting the decision
not to wear my haori, though.
[HOTARO]
Haori?
[ERU] It's a coat that you
wear over your kimono.
[HOTARO]
Right.
I really wish I had worn
a trenchcoat myself
right about now.
[ERU] It feels like it's
getting chillier, too.
[HOTARO shivering]
[HOTARO]
I'm sorry, Chitanda.
We can't hold out much longer.
It has to have
reached Ibara by now,
but she hasn't
skipped out on work
to come investigate or anything.
[ERU]
That's okay.
I appreciate you indulging
my selfish request
for as long as you have.
[HOTARO] It isn't selfish.
It's your responsibility.
[ERU] That doesn't give me
an excuse to make you
suffer for it, too.
Let's call for help.
I can manage whatever
gossip might arise from it.
[ERU] Fukube should have
made it back by now, too.
[HOTARO gasps]
Yes, that's it! Satoshi's here!
[ERU]
Oreki?
[HOTARO] Chitanda, do you happen
to have any kind of string?
[ERU]
Um... Did you say string?
[HOTARO]
Yeah, about this much?
Fifty centimeters
is more than enough.
Once we get that,
I have a sure-fire way
of alerting Satoshi
to our situation.
[ERU]
The strap from my sandals?
[HOTARO]
Too short.
[ERU] Oh, what about the
drawstring from my purse?
[HOTARO] Can't use that.
We need your purse intact.
[ERU] Then why don't we
use one of your shoelaces?
[HOTARO] Sadly, I'm wearing
boots with no laces.
[ERU]
If there's no other choice,
then I might have an idea.
We could use the
obijime from my sash.
[HOTARO]
Is that a string?
[ERU]
Yes.
[HOTARO] Would taking it
off be difficult?
[ERU] It would be kind
of hard, I suppose.
But I think I'd
be able to manage.
[HOTARO] Sorry, Chitanda,
this may be awkward.
I don't know much about
kimonos, so bear with me.
If you took off the obijime ,
would the rest of the
kimono hold up okay?
[ERU]
Um, no, not exactly.
The sash would fall off.
[HOTARO]
What?! That's not an option!
[ERU] No, you're right,
I guess it's not.
[HOTARO groans]
Back to square one.
Well, is there any other
string around here?
[ERU]
If you don't mind my asking,
how are you going to
get help from Fukube
using a little bit of string?
[HOTARO] I think I remember
seeing a flag outside the shed.
[HOTARO]
Sorry 'bout this.
[pounding noise]
[ERU]
Oreki... What are...?
[HOTARO]
Bingo! I was right!
[HOTARO] Chitanda, I need to
borrow your purse for a minute.
[ERU] Okay, but what are
you going to do with it?
[MAYAKA]
What the--?!
This is definitely Chi's
purse, no doubt about it!
She had it before!
So, a handkerchief,
a wallet, and now a purse?
I'm willing to bet this is
Hotaro's bad luck hard at work.
The parishioners said they
found this by the shed, too!
What in the world is
going on with those guys,
and why's this old string
tied to the purse?
String?
[MAYAKA]
Yeah, check it out.
[SATOSHI]
This is...!
Whoa. What's the matter, Fuku?
Mayaka, quick!
Where is the shed?
It's over that way, right
next to the Inari statue.
[SATOSHI]
I'll be right back!
Hotaro, Chitanda!
Don't worry, here I come!
[HOTARO shivering]
[HOTARO]
Your purse is just a bag, right?
When you tie off the
opening and the bottom,
that closes up all the
contents inside of it.
You know the expression,
"like a rat trapped in a bag?"
[ERU]
"Like a rat trapped in a bag?"
[HOTARO] I'm not making
anything up, I promise.
The phrase was coined at
a famous historical event.
You've probably heard of the
Battle of Anegawa, haven't you?
[ERU]
Yes.
[HOTARO] There's a legendary
story that happened
right before that;
have you heard it?
The withdrawal
from Kanegazaki?
When Nobunaga was laying
siege to the Asakura clan,
his brother-in-law,
Azai, betrayed him.
Nobunaga's sister, Oichi,
sent a bean bag tied up at
both ends to him in the field,
to send the message that
she was a "rat in a bag."
I don't know how much of
the story is actually true,
but that's beside the point.
[ERU] I don't think I've
heard that story before.
[HOTARO] It just so
happens that Satoshi and I
both saw that episode
play out on a TV show today.
Knowing how his mind works,
he'll get what it means.
[knock on door]
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro! Are you in there?
[HOTARO]
Yeah!
You've saved us.
We were on the verge
of freezing to death.
[SATOSHI] They're serving hot
sweet saké at the office.
I'm opening the door now.
Hey.
Mis-Happy New Year, my friends.
[HOTARO chuckles]
Mis-Happy
New Year yourself, buddy.
[ERU sneezes]
[MAYAKA] Next time: "The Case
of the Homemade Chocolates."