[YOSHINO] So, Chitanda,
can you say with certainty
that you will catch
the phantom thief Jumoji?
[ERU]
Of course we will!
Well, that's our intention.
With all of your--
With everyone helping us out,
I don't think there's
any logical reason
that we wouldn't be
able to catch Jumoji!
Whoa, that's a
pretty bold statement!
Then my next question:
What do you think
Jumoji is after now?
[ERU] Well, we've already
gotten something ready
that fits his pattern of thefts:
proofed manuscripts.
[YOSHINO]
Proofed manuscripts?
[ERU]
Yes.
Corrected drafts of the Classic
Lit Club's anthology, Hyouka .
[MAYAKA]
Huh?
Are there fewer of them?
[ERU] Our anthology contains
a story no less compelling
than the Jumoji Caper,
so come pick one up!
Because if you like
mystery as much as we do,
you'll love this tale
that will keep you
on the edge of your seat!
Wow, that does sound
pretty intriguing!
[ERU]
Yes.
Everyone!
Please come check out
the Classic Lit Club's
anthology, Hyouka !
It's great! I know
you're all gonna love it!
Thanks!
One more thing,
as we're getting ready to roll
out the red carpet for Jumoji,
we'd like to ask
everyone for a small favor.
[YOSHINO]
Oh, yeah? And what's that?
[ERU] Well, since there are
only four of us in the club,
we need help keeping
an eye on everything.
So everyone, if you
have some free time,
come help the Classic Lit Club!
And I mean everyone!
We are counting on
all of you to help!
[YOSHINO]
I understand!
Strength in numbers, am I right?
Yes!
We expect everyone
to come help us out!
Thanks in advance!
Hmm... I've always been a
sucker for a desperate request!
[ERU gasps]
Another thing...
...if you come by and
you think you can...
...please buy
an anthology. Okay?
And so, the final target,
the Classic Lit Club,
is more than ready to engage!
Well, Chitanda, happy hunting!
[ERU]
Thank you for your time.
We hope you all decide
to stand with us.
[YOSHINO]
That was Eru Chitanda, everyone!
[BROADCAST CLUB BOY 16A]
Okay, we're off the air.
[ERU sighs]
Hey, that was a
decent interview!
[ERU]
Thank you very much.
[YOSHINO]
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just not sure if I
should be doing all of this.
[sighs]
One, please.
200 yen.
[BOY 17B]
One, please.
[HOTARO] Whoa! They're
selling! This is great!
We're so close.
Almost sold out.
[BOY 17C] Do you think
he's really coming?
[GIRL 17B] As packed as
this place is right now,
he couldn't make his move!
[GIRL 17C]
Yeah, you're right.
It'd be impossible like this.
How long do you think this thief
is going to make us wait?
Does Jumoji even exist?
[BOY 17E] Could they be doing
all of this themselves?
[GIRL 17E] Yeah, I hadn't
even thought of that!
[BOY 17F] Show yourself,
already, Jumoji.
--[cell phone ringing]
--[STUDENTS gasp]
[SATOSHI] Sorry about that.
Just my cell phone.
[MAYAKA]
Geez.
You gonna answer?
Nah. Not till after
our watch--
[STUDENTS gasp, scream]
[BOY 17A]
Hey, it's on fire!
It's on fire!
[BOY 17C]
Put it out! Put it out!
[coughs]
[STUDENTS whispering]
[ERU]
Water?
[SATOSHI]
We've been had.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Look. He left this.
[SATOSHI] It's Jumoji's
confession note, all right.
[BOY 17G] I hate to say,
"I told you so."
[BOY 17A] Wait, you never
said this would happen!
[BOY 17B]
He got them good, huh?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GIRL 17A] Now I'm thinking
Jumoji might be a girl!
[GIRL 17B] Huh?
What makes you say that?
[GIRL 17A]
I mean, just think about it.
[chattering continues]
We sold out.
Huh?
I'm sorry I couldn't sell
them at the list price.
No, don't worry!
This is great!
Thanks so much. I mean it.
Really, you have no idea!
[IRISU] Oh, stand up.
And another thing...
[ERU]
Yes?
I don't know if I
should tell you this...
Should tell me what?
[IRISU]
I heard your radio broadcast.
[ERU] Oh, did you think that I
followed your advice correctly?
[IRISU]
Look, about that...
My advice was
a bit too literal.
I want to be clear about this.
You aren't really suited
for stuff like that.
When you try so
hard to manipulate
the expectations of others,
you come across
as kind of needy.
[ERU]
Needy?
Do you really think
that's how I sounded?
[IRISU] Maybe as much as
the tip of my little finger.
However, sometimes, if you
pretend to be something,
you wind up becoming that way
in your real life somehow.
[ERU]
Right.
You'd really do better
to not take my words
at face value if you're only
going to botch the execution.
You might see your
inability to manipulate
as a shortcoming, but under
the right circumstances,
it's a valuable weapon.
So... You understand?
Yes. I was kind of
thinking the same thing!
I'm just not cut out
for this sort of stuff.
I guess, what I mean is...
Well... I've had enough.
[GIRL 17F]
That was exciting.
[TANI] Wow, not even
the Classic Lit Club
could catch Jumoji, huh?
I expected so much from you.
[SATOSHI]
Yeah, well...
Sorry I haven't lived up
to your expectations.
No way.
It was still an entertaining
cultural festival.
Plus, I got my revenge
for the cooking competition.
See ya.
Who's he?
That's Tani.
He doesn't get the
subtleties of language.
You know?
What do you mean?
He said "expected."
That's not really what
you say to your opponent
when neither of you won.
Why does that matter?
"Expected"--
Using that word implies
that it's finished.
If you still believe in
yourself, it's not appropriate.
The way he phrased it...
It's not right,
'cause this isn't over.
Unless there's no hope,
and things have gone
worse than imagined,
there's no point
in using that word.
Fukube...
Anyway, the cards
haven't all fallen.
[SATOSHI] I swear I saw
Hotaro come this way.
[SATOSHI]
There he is.
Let's cut to the chase,
then, shall we?
You are Jumoji, aren't you?
You might as well confess.
What? Just a shot in the dark?
[SATOSHI]
Tanabe's Jumoji?
First, there's your card.
Why does it always say "lost,"
rather than "stolen" or "taken?"
Who knows?
My next question deals
with the letter "ku."
Why did you skip it?
That alone should
eliminate the Jumoji theory,
but what if it dealt
with some element
that the rest of the school
didn't know anything about?
Something not meant
for the public.
[TANABE]
Oh? Like what?
The Jumoji Caper itself.
The entire affair was
only a code, wasn't it?
You had to deliver a message,
to one whose name
starts with "ku,"
and something beginning with
"ku" had already been lost.
It was two-fold.
That's a convoluted code
for relaying a message.
[HOTARO]
A layman could never crack it,
but if the recipient already
knew the rules of the cipher,
it would be easy.
To cut right to the chase...
I believe that was the plot
of The Kudryavka Sequence ,
the manga you were
all planning to write.
You're wondering how on
Earth I could know the title.
Isn't that right?
The Kudryavka Sequence
is a take on
one of Agatha Christie's
most famous works,
The A.B.C. Murders.
Same goes for the Jumoji Caper.
The culprit used The
Kudryavka Sequence
as his source material.
As for the intended recipient
of the coded message,
that's Muneyoshi Kugayama.
Student council president.
And the artist behind
A Corpse by Evening .
Am I wrong?
Hmm...
Why would all the
other targets be clubs,
and then switch
it up to have "ku"
represent someone's name?
Jumoji never wrote
anything to establish
that all the targets
would be clubs.
It's a bit thin.
[HOTARO]
It's not that thin at all.
You put out a list,
and implied that all
of your victims
would be chosen from
among those on it.
Copying the timetable bit
from The A.B.C. Murders
was obvious.
I mean, you had a list
already drawn up for you.
All the victims were together,
right here on this page.
The Acapella Club, the Go Club,
the Fortunetelling Club,
the Gardening Club,
the Cooking Club,
the Wall Newspaper Club,
the Magic Club, and finally...
...Muneyoshi Kugayama.
Once I put it all together,
it wasn't difficult
to trace back to you.
It's incredibly convenient
that all the targeted clubs
were listed together
on this page.
Only someone on
the executive committee
could have orchestrated
this page that way.
Fine, but there are 20 other
people on that committee.
Yes. That brings me
to the manga.
A Corpse by Evening .
President Kugayama, the author,
had teamed up with
Haruna Anjo on this one,
so he must have known about
The Kudryavka Sequence .
That means President
Kugayama would also
be able to decipher
the Jumoji Caper's code.
One possibility is that Kugayama
lost the original story
for The Kudryavka Sequence ,
thus providing a motive.
Jumoji could have concocted
this whole scheme
in order to exact
revenge for that, right?
Meaning the message
he was trying to relay
with these crimes is this:
"Kugayama has already forfeited
his Kudryavka Sequence."
Now, consider this afterword:
It was written by the
same person who helped
with the backgrounds.
Haruna Anjo.
President Kugayama.
Other than those two,
only one other person
knows the plot line of The
Kudryavka Sequence .
That person is the only
possible culprit here,
and then there's this:
"Takuha Ajimu."
That's quite an odd penname.
But it's just a mash-up
of the first characters
in the names of the three
people who wrote this, right?
[TANABE]
How's that?
[HOTARO] "Haruna Anjo"
gives us "Ha" and "A."
"Muneyoshi Kugayama."
There's the "Mu" and "Ku."
Take away those four letters,
and you're left with two
characters: "Ji" and "Ta."
It has to be a
second year or higher,
someone who was at last
year's cultural festival,
on the executive committee,
and whose initials
are "Ji" and "Ta."
We also can deduce
that it has to be someone
who knows President
Kugayama well enough
to know he draws manga.
There's only one person
who fits that bill.
And that would be you.
Jiro Tanabe.
Well done, sir.
I never imagined in
my wildest dreams
that anyone other than Mune
or Anjo would be able
to crack my little code.
I'll be damned.
Expectations, smashed.
Way to go.
[HOTARO] Why did you use
such a roundabout way
to send your message?
[TANABE]
I think you know the answer.
Is it because of your
feelings for Haruna Anjo,
who was transferred
to another school?
[TANABE laughs]
That was a part of it.
It's also just that it
was the cultural festival.
I was dying to pull off
a well-executed prank.
Although...
...not being able
to say it out loud...
That was the biggest reason.
[clears throat]
Well, there's another
matter I'd like to discuss.
I just have a small request
to make of you, Tanabe.
Yeah? What's that?
I'd like you to
buy these from me.
Thirty copies of Hyouka ,
our anthology.
Are you blackmailing
me into buying these
in exchange for your silence?
[HOTARO]
Yep.
I'm actually asking the
executive committee to buy them.
[TANABE]
That's absurd.
[HOTARO]
There's nothing absurd about it.
This is Kami High's website.
That's a mail-order link,
a place to buy items
from the cultural
festival, right?
You could have the executive
committee buy these,
then resell them through
this link on the website.
I can't just agree
to resell them
without a good reason.
There has to be some kind
of buzz about them first.
Absolutely.
But lucky for us, there's
already a good deal of hype
around Hyouka .
What are you talking about?
[HOTARO] Don't you know?
Jumoji, of course.
The Classic Lit Club is going
to be your final target.
I can help,
and Satoshi Fukube
will also be an accomplice
once I officially ask him.
You'll have inside
men at the target.
You couldn't ask
for an easier job.
People will flock to
the Classic Lit Club room
to try to catch Jumoji
at his last target.
The anthologies will
fly off the shelves,
creating a demand
for them online,
and then you'll sell them there.
It gives you the
perfect opportunity
to wrap up your scheme
in a nice little package.
What do you say?
[TANABE]
That's not bad.
Yeah, I like the sound of it!
A dramatic close
to the Jumoji Caper,
and also providing items
for the mail order site.
It's beneficial
to both parties.
[sighs]
I'm glad we agree.
[TANABE] So how do you plan
to aid and abet Jumoji
in his crimes?
[HOTARO] We'll prepare
a proofed manuscript,
which will be your target.
Then we'll post guards
to surround it,
so no one can get close.
[TANABE]
Oh? Then what?
According to the guidebook,
the Chemistry Club
is doing a demonstration
on what happens
when water is poured
directly over pure sodium.
I saw a video
of it once online.
It flares up, and looks
pretty spectacular.
You don't plan on
doing that, do you?
[HOTARO]
I do.
I want you to somehow
get ahold of the sodium.
Once you do that,
we'll need water pistols.
Some members of the Confection
Club are carrying them around.
You'll have to negotiate
with them for one.
You sure play a
dangerous game, don't you?
It's festival week.
Why don't we close
it out with a bang?
[chuckles]
All right.
[HOTARO] Then after we get the
sodium, I'll figure out a way
to slip some of it
into the manuscript pages.
Once we sell enough copies,
I'll give you a signal,
like this,
and that's when I want
you to shoot the pages
with the water pistol.
But everyone's going to
be watching the manuscript
like hawks, aren't they?
Yeah, that's true.
Okay, how about this:
I'll get Satoshi to put
his cell phone by the door.
Just call it before you
shoot the manuscript,
and it will divert
people's attention.
They won't know what hit them.
[TANABE]
Good idea.
What should we do
about the confession note?
The room will probably
devolve into chaos,
so just slip it into
a copy of Hyouka
and drop it on the floor.
That sounds good.
All right, well, you'll have
to buy a copy to do that.
That'll be 200 yen.
[chuckles]
You're quite the salesman.
We really are up a creek here,
so I'm desperate.
What did you say
your name was, again?
I'm Hotaro Oreki.
I'm from Class 1-B.
Are "expectations"
what pop into your mind
when you think about Oreki?
That's astute.
What gave it away?
[MAYAKA]
I can just tell by watching.
Only when it comes
to you, though.
[MAYAKA] Fuku, were you
trying to beat Oreki?
[SATOSHI] It's not that
I want to beat him.
I just look up to him a lot.
But...
I don't expect you to
understand that, Mayaka.
[MAYAKA]
No, I think I get it.
[SATOSHI]
Well, I really messed this up.
I forgot my main rule.
Databases can't ever
come up with conclusions.
[KUGAYAMA] And so,
the 54th Kanyasai closes
without incident.
Although...
...there were a number
of "odd occurrences."
[STUDENTS laughing]
Way to go! [laughs]
[KUGAYAMA] Anyway,
good work all around, folks.
I hereby declare the 54th annual
Kamiyama High School Cultural
Festival officially closed!
[STUDENTS cheering, clapping]
[MAYAKA] I know this may
be too little, too late,
but I brought it.
This manga was written
by someone whom I believe
will someday
write a masterpiece.
[KOCHI sighs]
You actually found a copy.
Yes.
This isn't mine, though.
I borrowed it.
But Kochi, you already knew
about this manga, didn't you?
Yuasa told you.
That jerk.
[MAYAKA]
She did.
Yuasa said that you
and the author used to be
close friends or something.
[KOCHI]
Friends? Yeah, that's right.
I wonder how Haruna
is doing these days.
It's been a while
since I've heard from her.
Have you ever read this manga?
[MAYAKA]
I have to say...
I think I understand what
you said a little better now.
That whether or not
a manga is appealing
is ultimately
a subjective matter.
I get it, but I still
don't think you're right
across the board.
I mean, that would
take all the hope
and fun out of reading,
wouldn't it?
A Corpse by Evening
is a perfect example.
It's a really serious title.
If I were only into gag manga,
I wouldn't even give it
a second thought.
That's just how people are.
But if they did read it,
they would like it!
Some works have a powerful
impact on people, regardless!
On those with
discerning tastes, maybe.
I don't agree!
I'm messing with you.
I'm joking.
Come on, I feel the same
way you do about manga.
You're just too
passionate to see it.
You're so sincere.
It's all bluster.
Ayako doesn't mean it.
[KOCHI] That manga keeps
coming back to haunt me,
so I guess I'm supposed
to have this conversation.
I haven't read the whole thing.
I gave up halfway.
Know why?
[MAYAKA]
I don't.
[KOCHI] You told me before that
I would understand if I read it.
And I get it, I really do.
It's good.
But I don't actually want to
have to admit that it's good.
It's all about my pride.
Say you had a friend
who didn't read manga,
but knew you
were really into it.
Then that friend
teamed up with someone.
And decided to draw one herself.
So?
If it were great, wouldn't
you be a little angry?
[KOCHI] That's why I keep it
tucked in the back of my closet.
I swore I'd never read it.
Out of spite and pettiness,
I refused to open it.
I swore to always say
that it was no good.
But fate just had to keep
throwing it in my face.
Look, I'm sorry you went
and got a copy for me,
because I am still
not gonna read it.
[MAYAKA]
Wait...
[KOCHI]
I mean, if I were to read it,
then I'd be forced
to reach out to her.
And how could I bring
myself to say,
"I read it, and you're amazing!
I have really high expectations
for your next one!"
I can't make myself do that!
You know?
[MAYAKA] That cat...
It's from Body Talk !
A masterpiece is a
masterpiece from the beginning.
It doesn't become one.
[MAYAKA]
Body Talk .
There's no denying it's a step
below A Corpse by Evening .
My stuff is a
hundred steps below.
[MAYAKA crying]
[ERU] Is this pile really
all that's left of them?
--[HOTARO] Yeah.
--[SATOSHI] Whoa... Whoa!
I can't believe it!
I can't believe we
pulled this off!
[ERU]
It's incredible!
We sold almost 200 anthologies!
I never expected to do that!
"Expected."
Interesting.
Oh... nothing.
[HOTARO]
I can't ever tell Chitanda
that I resorted to blackmail
to sell these things.
[TANABE]
Hey, Oreki.
Earlier, you mentioned you
thought that the reason
I started this whole thing
was to get revenge
on Kugayama for losing
the Kudryavka Sequence ,
isn't that right?
It was just a hypothesis.
I have no real way of knowing
what your true motive was
in doing it.
Well, it's astute.
Especially because
Anjo is the only person
who truly knows how I feel.
Wait, are you saying
Kugayama has no idea?
Yeah.
But the code was
invented and executed
with him in mind, right?
[TANABE]
That's correct.
[HOTARO]
Then what's the point?
[TANABE]
Ever since Mune--I mean,
ever since Kugayama finished
A Corpse by Evening ,
he hasn't picked up his pen
to write again, not even once.
Anjo is brilliant, too,
don't get me wrong,
but I had no idea Kugayama
could draw so well.
I wish I had his talent,
but I'm mediocre at best.
[growls] I couldn't
hold a candle to him!
I know the story isn't lost!
I think that if he would just
get his head in the right place,
he could create a masterpiece
that would blow
A Corpse by Evening
out of the water!
But as far as Mune is concerned,
drawing manga is something
he just did once on a lark.
[HOTARO]
He did that on a lark?
It's such a waste of talent.
You think it's a
shame, too, right?
But he doesn't have
any desire to draw.
I would have been willing
to do anything he said,
anything to help,
if he would just agree
to continue working on it.
But I was too afraid
to speak up.
I didn't want to admit
to myself that he might not
recognize the message.
And out of that denial,
my expectations were born.
I've been carrying them
around this whole time.
[HOTARO] But wouldn't it
have been a lot simpler
if you could just
tell him how you feel?
If you had asked him?
"Kugayama.
Have you even had a chance to
read The Kudryavka Sequence " ?
You really are perceptive.
[HOTARO]
But you know his answer.
[TANABE]
Oh, you're right. I do.
Mune never opened the
story that Anjo poured
her heart and soul into.
So he couldn't have
cracked the code.
[TANABE]
My message didn't get through.
[MAYAKA]
Oreki.
Here, thanks for this.
Tell your sister
I said thanks, too.
Yeah.
What now?
Nothing. I'll tell her for you.
[ERU] So what should
we do about these
four leftover copies?
[SATOSHI]
There's nothing much we can do.
I guess we'll just have
to buy one copy each.
[ALL laugh]
[ERU]
And with that... we're sold out!
[ALL cheering]
[cheering continues]
All that's left is to find the
truth behind the Jumoji Caper.
And now, since there's
nothing standing in our way...
...we can use all
of our brain power!
Or... not.
Oh.
Actually, Hotaro already
figured that one out.
Leave it to him to
crack it on his own.
Huh? Did he really?
Is that true?
Well... I mean...
Yeah, why don't you tell us all
about your findings, Hotaro?
We can have our own little
selling-out celebration.
Oh!
Satoshi!
Come on, buddy, why don't
we all have some fun?
[HOTARO]
Huh?
[MAYAKA]
I am so down to party!
I didn't get to spend much time
with the Classic Lit Club.
So you have to tell me
everything that happened!
[ERU] Okay, why don't you guys
all come over to my place, then?
[SATOSHI]
All right, it's settled!
[HOTARO]
Wait, what's settled?
[MAYAKA] Yes! Time to get
out of here and cut loose!
We are drinking tonight!
[HOTARO]
Now we're drinking?
[MAYAKA]
Oolong tea, dummy!
[HOTARO] That's the lamest
thing I've ever heard.
[ERU] Next time: "Is the
Mountain Range Clear?"