[QUIZ CLUB PRESIDENT]
All right, everyone!
Are you ready?
[CROWD cheering]
Who's our next quiz king?
Do you wanna know?
[CROWD]
Yeah!
Then let's get started
with the prelim round!
You with me?
[CROWD]
Yeah!
Quiz... trial... 7!
--[CROWD cheering]
--[SATOSHI] Yeah!
Question number one!
Here we go: "The term
"adamant" refers to a diamond,
while the term "beryl"
refers to an emerald."
So is this true, or is it false?
[SATOSHI] Not a terrible
first question, I guess.
The answer is...
...it's true!
[CROWD cheering]
[SATOSHI] Time to show off my
database skills.
Let's do this.
[ANNOUNCER 13A] There aren't
very many contestants left now.
Will question 7 be the last
of the prelim round?
Let's see!
[ANNOUNCER 13A] The word
"darui," or "listless",
derives from the
English word "dull."
Is this true, or is it false?
[ONODERA]
What do you think?
[KIMURA] Well, it makes
sense that it would be,
but I don't know.
[ONODERA]
What's your answer, Mayaka?
[MAYAKA]
Huh?
[ONODERA] Do you think
it's true or false?
Maybe... it's true?
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
The answer is...
[SATOSHI] The suspense is
killing me!
...false!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 13A] And that's it
for the preliminaries!
[SATOSHI]
Wa-hoo!
If you answered correctly,
congratulations!
The championship round will
be held right over here!
Come on up!
[TANI]
Yo!
Wow, man.
That's one serious hat
you're rockin' there.
[SATOSHI]
Who's he again?
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
[TANI] You didn't even realize I
was competing, did you?
[SATOSHI laughs] I was pretty
focused on the quiz.
[SATOSHI]
Oh, I remember him!
So, Tani, how's the Go Club?
The Go Club.
I've got a funny story
about that, actually.
Wanna hear it?
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Fantastic!
Now, let's hear from
our third finalist.
[SATOSHI]
Yeah, I'm coming!
We should go.
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Whoa!
Looks like there's a
giant Saturn on his head!
[ANNOUNCER 13A] Please tell
us your name and class.
Hello, folks. Satoshi Fukube!
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Ooh!
From the Classic Lit Club!
Wow!
We have a Classic Lit Club?
Who knew?
Based on that outfit,
your club must be wild, huh?
Yeah!
Sure! We are totally wild!
I mean really, we've done a lot
of awesome stuff this year.
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
You have?
Please, tell us more!
[SATOSHI] Well, we knew that we
needed to create an anthology,
and we wanted to
make the most of it.
Honestly, I think the results
are pretty amazing.
We put everything into it!
[HOTARO] Oh, yeah. We put
everything into it, money-wise.
As a matter of fact, we
uncovered a long-buried secret
about this very festival!
[SATOSHI laughs]
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Please, tell us more!
We found the origin
of the term "Kanyasai."
It is not just a
simple abbreviation
of "Kamiyama High School
Cultural Festival."
The Classic Lit Club...
...has found the truth!
[CROWD cheering]
What is the name's origin?
To find out...
...buy our anthology!
For the low price of 200 yen,
you can learn the
45-year-old secret
of Kami High's
cultural festival.
Purchase your copy
of Hyouka now
in the Earth Science Prep Room
on the 4th floor of
the auxiliary building!
[CROWD cheering]
[SATOSHI]
Pitch successful!
At this point,
winning is just gravy.
[ERU]
I'm here, Oreki!
How'd it go?
I talked to Tanabe.
He said we could ask other
clubs to sell copies for us
at their booths.
My first thought
was to find Irisu
and ask if she would
consider helping us out,
but I never quite made it there.
[HOTARO]
Yeah. I think I can see why.
What should we do now?
Satoshi's plug
was pretty effective.
Maybe that'll do the trick.
Huh? A plug!
That's it!
I heard the Wall Newspaper Club
is putting out an extra edition!
I'll go ask them
if they'll cover
the Classic Lit Club in it.
[HOTARO]
Always on the move.
[ERU]
Excuse me!
[TOGAITO]
Hey, Chitanda. Need something?
[ERU] Actually, yes.
I could use your help.
Could you cover the
Classic Lit Club in your extra?
Huh?
I'm confused.
What is it that
you want, exactly?
A small favor.
The club's run
into some trouble.
I was hoping you might
write a promotional article
for us and publish it
in the wall newspaper.
Oh. Uh...
I dunno.
The thing is, I'm not
really in the club anymore.
Since it's my last year
of school, I've retired.
All right, I'm sorry.
Well, then, is there a chance
you could introduce me
to the people who
are running it now?
Sure, I don't mind doing that,
but it may not do you any good.
The one-page extra is
set to run in two hours.
So the layout is pretty
much fixed at this point.
So it's impossible
to add anything?
For today, anyway.
But they might have
some room available
if you can wait until
the afternoon on day 2.
That said, there are more
than 50 clubs at Kanyasai,
and the paper gives priority
to those that deserve
the most attention.
And I'm not sure your
club makes the cut.
No offense, but all you're doing
is publishing an
anthology, right?
Yes, but, there's
important information in it.
Come on, every club thinks
that what it does is important.
Tell you what: if you can
come up with a story
that's actually going to
capture people's interest,
I'll personally ask them
to run it, okay?
Yes. I understand.
Well, thank you,
and I'm sorry for taking up
so much of your time.
[TOGAITO] Remember, if you come
up with an interesting story,
drop by again.
I may be able to help you out.
[KAHO]
Eru?
[ERU gasps]
[ERU]
Hi, Kaho!
[KAHO]
Long time no see.
[ERU]
How is Uncle Jumonji doing,
after everything that happened?
[KAHO]
He's doing fine now.
How about you, though?
You look kinda stressed.
I guess so.
I've got a lot going on.
Well, maybe I can help.
I'll tell your fortune
if you want.
This is a pretty amazing
setup you've got here.
A lot of options, too.
I think I'd like to try
a tarot reading.
Oh. I'm sorry, I can't do that.
[ERU]
Really? But why not?
Eru... You like a
good mystery, right?
[ERU]
What is that?
I'm running this all by myself,
so I have to leave the
booth unattended sometimes.
I stepped out for a little bit,
and when I came back,
the Wheel of Fortune card was
missing from my Tarot deck.
And that card had
been left in its place.
[ERU] It says "Jumonji."
I don't get it.
Why would your last name
be written on here?
[KAHO]
Good question. I wish I knew.
Have you been able
to track down the card
that disappeared yet?
I think I'll get
it back eventually.
This note was left here, too.
I don't think I've ever
heard of a thief
who puts things back before.
Here. If you don't mind,
there's one more thing
I'd like to show you.
[ERU]
A festival guidebook?
Is there something
special about it?
As far as I can tell,
it's the same as all the others.
I found it here the same
time I found that card.
When I noticed it,
it was open to the last page--
the one with all the
club comments on it.
This is so strange.
What do you think it means?
I have no idea,
but as long as I get my
Wheel of Fortune back safely,
I'm willing to
let it go at that.
[ANNOUNCER 13A] It's almost
time to crown a winner!
So is everybody ready?
Shimizu and Goto
both have 5 points.
Meanwhile...
Tani and Fukube have 6 points,
and both of them seem
eager to clinch the title.
Which of our four competitors
will be the champion?
Before we find out,
let's give them all a hand!
[CROWD cheering]
All right,
on to the next question.
Get ready!
The formula to determine
the surface area of a sphere...
...is 4 pi r squared.
Oho! Quick one!
I haven't even finished
the question yet!
Are you sure about this?
I'm sure.
All right, then.
Shimizu, what's your answer?
The answer is 4/3 pi r cubed.
[ANNOUNCER 13A squealing]
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Correct!
[SHIMIZU]
Hooray!
The formula used to
determine the surface area
of a sphere is 4 pi r squared.
Now, please tell us the formula
used to determine its volume.
That formula is 4/3 pi r cubed.
Quite impressive!
Shimizu now has 6 points.
Three contestants are
a step away from winning!
It's almost too
exciting to handle!
You hang in there, Goto!
All right.
On to our next question.
Get ready!
Kami High School's student
council president's full name...
...is what, contestants?
Yes? What is your answer?
Muneyoshi Kugayama.
[CLUB 13A squealing]
[SATOSHI] Seriously, can
we just get on with it?
Correct!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
Let's give it up for...
Oh, well. Good game.
Huh? Yeah.
It was a close one.
For both of us.
You're right.
Then I guess we're even.
Yep. Guess we are.
I never did finish
telling you that story.
Some of our Go stones were
stolen from our room.
Really?
You sure they were stolen
and not just lost?
There was a strange note left
in the Go stone bowl saying,
"We've taken some stones
from the Go Club."
And it's not like we
use all of them,
so they could easily take 10,
and nobody would notice
they were missing.
But what's the point of stealing
them in the first place?
I'd say they're probably using
them to play Five-in-a-Row.
It sounds like some other
club is messing with you.
[CROWD cheering]
Well... bye.
Not so fast, Fukube.
I can't just let
this end in a tie.
Let's settle it for good.
Where are you competing next?
I'm doing the
cooking club tomorrow.
You're on!
The Cooking Club will
decide who the true winner is.
Looking forward to it!
You're the winner!
--How does it feel?
--[SATOSHI] What's his deal?
[SATOSHI] I couldn't care less
about competing against Tani.
I wonder if Hotaro
is hard at work...
[GARDENING CLUB 13A]
You open?
[HOTARO gasps]
Oh, yeah. Sure, we're open.
I hear there are some
cool Kanyasai facts
in your little book.
You mind if I look through it?
I do, actually.
They're cheap enough, okay?
Please buy one.
We've got so many copies,
its killing us.
[laughs]
I don't know if
you realized, man,
but your fly's unzipped.
Huh? Oh, crap!
Aww...
The whole zipper's torn off.
What am I gonna do?
You can have this if
you want. It might help.
Oh, hey!
Lucky you've got one of
these hanging around.
You're a lifesaver. [chuckles]
[GARDENING CLUB 13A]
I'll tell ya what.
Take this.
That's not a real gun, is it?
Of course not.
It's a water gun.
I'm in the gardening club.
We've been roasting
sweet potatoes.
These seemed like a cooler way
to put out fires than buckets.
In that case, shouldn't you
probably hang onto this?
Nah, I'm good.
That's just my sidearm.
This is my main
weapon right here.
AK, baby.
[HOTARO]
"Baby"?
Well, later, man.
Thanks for the help.
[HOTARO] A Glock 17.
Just what I always wanted.
[KOCHI] I'm telling you...
it's no use.
This collection was
doomed from the start.
We're not exactly
drawing a crowd.
We should start
making up posters.
Maybe that way, we can at
least get a few customers.
I know.
It's frustrating,
but we all decided
that this is what
we wanted to do.
[MAYAKA]
Why is everybody looking at me?
[KOCHI]
I mean, 100 manga reviews?
It's not like this
is classic literature
we're talking about, here.
Please, Kochi. Just stop.
I don't see why anyone would
bother to read reviews of manga.
It's a waste of time. Right?
[MATSUYO]
I... um, I don't know.
[MAYAKA] There's probably no
chance Fuku will believe me,
but I really was trying
to behave myself.
What do you mean,
"why would anyone bother?"
I'm confused.
The fact is, all manga
is basically the same.
Are you serious?
Sure, I am.
One manga is just
as good as another,
so reviewing them
is totally pointless.
You don't think
the writing matters?
[KOCHI]
No, I don't.
[MAYAKA] If that's true, how are
people supposed to decide
which one they want to read?
This isn't
rocket science, Ibara.
People read what they're into.
Just think about it: a sports
fan will read about sports,
and a romantic will
read about romance.
It's as simple as that.
You're saying that people will
read about what interests them,
without caring whether
or not it's any good.
Exactly!
Which is why I don't
think there's any point
in writing reviews.
Everyone should just
read what they like.
This is entertainment,
not fine art.
[MAYAKA]
All manga is basically the same?
I can't let that
statement stand.
I'll prove her wrong.
[MAYAKA]
Let me clarify.
To you, no manga stands
out above the rest,
meaning there are no works that
can be considered masterpieces.
There are masterpieces.
[MAYAKA]
And how would you define them?
Well, there are series
that go on for many years
without losing popularity, even
gaining readers over time.
That makes them masterpieces.
I think you're wrong.
A masterpiece is a
masterpiece from the beginning.
It doesn't become one.
I don't see how a manga
can possibly deserve
that title until it's
stood the test of time.
That's just ignorant!
Excuse me?
It's a matter of
personal experience.
Tell me this...
Have you ever read something
that really got to you?
That made you laugh
or cry so much it hurt?
Wow, Ibara.
Aren't you a passionate one...
There's a big gap between
the skill and talent
of different artists.
For example...
There was a manga sold
at last year's cultural festival
that was titled A Corpse by
Evening . Have you read it?
No, I haven't.
Okay, then I'll
bring it in tomorrow.
And if reading that still
doesn't convince you,
then nothing I could
say ever would.
[MAYAKA]
Nice.
That pretty much guarantees
I won't be able
to leave copies of Hyouka here.
[MANGA CLUB VISITOR A]
I'll take one, please.
[YUASA]
Here you go. Thanks a lot.
[MAYAKA]
Were they all listening?
Hi! Thanks for coming!
[ERU] Battle of the Maidens?
Sounds interesting.
[ERU]
Excuse me.
What's up?
What is that?
Sorry, it's over now.
They'll go at it again
tomorrow, though.
So feel free to stop by then.
Sure.
[SATOSHI]
So... What did you think?
About my plug, I mean.
Did it help our
situation at all?
[HOTARO]
Yeah, I suppose.
We sold 14.
Yeah? That many?
Guess this means
publicity really works.
[SATOSHI] It looks like we're
off to a pretty good start.
I'll try to do it
again tomorrow.
The cooking contest should give
me a nice opportunity.
You mean the
"three-person team" competition?
Huh?
[SATOSHI] It's a team
competition?! Seriously?
[HOTARO] Shouldn't someone on
the executive committee
know these little details?
[ERU]
I struck out.
I didn't increase our
number of outlets,
and I couldn't get the
newspaper to do a story on us.
I'm sorry I failed.
[HOTARO]
Don't beat yourself up.
Although...
I did hear something that I'm
kind of curious about.
[HOTARO]
Of course you did.
[ERU]
Never mind.
It's nothing.
Just forget about it.
[HOTARO]
That's a great idea.
[SATOSHI]
See?
It doesn't say anything about
three-person teams!
I don't know what to tell ya.
I heard it straight from one of
the girls in the Cooking Club.
[SATOSHI]
Aww... What am I gonna do?
I thought I could
enter on my own.
What about you, Mayaka?
How did it go with
the Manga Club?
Just fine, thank you very much.
Ladies... Can I ask a favor?
Would you please
consider entering
the Cooking Club
contest with me?
I can ask the
Manga Club president
if she'll give me time
away from our booth.
If it'll help with publicity,
I'm definitely in.
Great!
If we work hard,
I know we can win it!
It sounds like you're
really invested in this.
Well, I am fairly proud
of my cooking ability.
And honestly, I would hate to
pass up a chance to show it off.
[bell ringing]
[PA ANNOUNCER 13A] Attention,
all students and visitors.
We hope you had
an excellent time.
This announcement marks the end
of our Kanyasai's first day,
and what a fantastic one it was!
Oreki, this envelope...
You didn't look, right?
Uh... No way.
Yeah. Of course.
I was just checking.
[MAYAKA]
Where is it?
Not here.
Where could it have gone?
[MAYAKA]
I guess I'll bring this instead.
No! I'll find it!
I've looked everywhere.
[MAYAKA]
Where is it?
[ERU]
Next time: "Wild Fire."