If this is already up
this early in the morning,
they must have kicked
it into high gear.
Well...
When it comes to high gear,
I can't be beat.
Yo, Fukube!
You're a little late
this morning.
Hi. Guess I am.
[SATOSHI]
Aw, bummer.
It's gonna be hard to keep
Jumoji at large at this rate.
Anyway...
You're pretty determined if
you're staking out this early.
Same for you.
[SATOSHI] Judging by the fact
that there are this many
amateur detectives around,
the crime must not
have happened yet.
All right, Jumoji.
If you're gonna strike,
bring it on!
[ERU] It's the last day of the
festival: the moment of truth.
Interesting.
She seems familiar.
I wonder if I've met her
somewhere before.
[HOTARO] The idea to use Jumoji
to sell copies of Hyouka
isn't necessarily a bad one.
But I'm not convinced
it's a good enough plan
to sell all of them.
I hope I'm wrong about that.
I'm just not convinced yet.
Nothing's happening here.
[SATOSHI]
He's right about that.
Is Jumoji's next
target the Quiz Club?
That doesn't make sense.
Why steal something from
them when their event
is already over?
This is boring.
I'm outta here.
[BOY 16B]
Yeah, man. This scene's over.
I'm gone.
[SATOSHI] What's wrong,
phantom thief Jumoji?
Were you scared off
by all the people?
[TANI]
Seriously?
Something you'd like to share?
Hmph. That dirty thief Jumoji
made a fool out of us.
Is that right?
Did he hit the Quiz Club?
Not them. Light Music Club.
Took one of their strings.
[SATOSHI]
Light Music Club?
Did I hear that right?
[SATOSHI] You're sure that's
good information?
If you don't believe me,
then why don't you just
investigate for yourself?
--Later.
--[SATOSHI] Hold on!
[SATOSHI]
It's no use.
[BOY 16C]
Check it out!
The Light Music Club got hit.
How did you know that?
[SATOSHI] Jumoji's adaptability
is more sophisticated
than I thought.
I might be a bit out
of my depth here.
My head-on approach
didn't work.
I have to go back to
the drawing board.
If I can't catch him in the act,
then how can I catch him?
[HOTARO]
Wow.
When they sell, they
sell out, don't they?
The 20 copies Chitanda gave
to Irisu are already gone,
so she brought another
ten down there.
Then I sold nine more
just this morning.
I'm starting to have
some hope about this.
That's Saturday for you.
[TOMOE]
Hey, there!
I see you've decided to take
on the easy work, as usual.
You're here?!
I didn't think you
would show up!
[TOMOE] What, you're not
grateful that your big sister
cares enough to come see how
her dear little
brother is doing?
Here.
Thank you for your patronage.
What's that?
It doesn't really suit you,
little bro.
[HOTARO]
Oh.
You can blame the
Warashibe protocol.
Your pen turned into
this little hand mirror.
[TOMOE]
What?
You mean you traded my pen
and ended up with that?
Pretty much.
I see. Well, then.
[TOMOE] I'll take it off your
hands, and in return you get...
...this.
[HOTARO]
What's that?
A Corpse by Evening .
It's a manga?
[TOMOE] Whether you decide to
spend your valuable time
reading it is
entirely up to you.
What's that supposed to mean?
[TOMOE]
Later, bro!
[HOTARO]
Hey, wait!
"Anshinin Takuha"?
[HOTARO] What do you think of
the way A Corpse by Evening
turned out?"
Well, if I do say so myself,
I think it turned out
very well."
Of course, all I did
was help out with
some of the backgrounds.
I didn't have much
to do with it at all."
"If you really enjoy
the finished product,
the credit goes to the
author and the artist,
least of all to me.
Credit where it's due,
you know?"
[HOTARO] I guess Anshinin
Takuha is just the name
they adopted for the whole team?
"It's not even as though
every single one of us
is in the Manga Club
or anything."
"We all just like manga a lot,
and really hit it off
when we would get
together to talk about it.
When we decided to try
making a manga of our own,
this is the story that emerged."
"I think it's kind
of extraordinary
for a maiden effort,
but that's my opinion.
I will let the creators toot
their own horns."
"I also want the reader to
decide for themselves,
without me putting
ideas in their heads."
"Now, keep in mind:
We have no intention
of breaking up the team
after just one title."
"We have already started
working on something new
with next year's
Kanyasai in mind."
"Our writer, A, is considering
turning the writing style
completely on its ear and
delving into the mystery genre."
"The word on the street is
that they plan to take on
one of Christie's
most famous works,
then see if there's any room for
a few twists here and there."
"The title has
already been chosen,
so I suppose I'll go ahead
and announce it here."
"The next story is
going to be called:
The Kudryavka Sequence ."
"We picked another
foreboding name."
"Okay, I look forward to
seeing you next year
during the Kanyasai season!
Anshinin Takuha."
[HOTARO]
The Kudryavka Sequence ?
I don't know what
"Kudryavka" means,
but the word "sequence"
captures my attention.
Also, which "one of Christie's
most famous works?"
[TOMOE] Whether you decide
to spend your valuable time
reading it is
entirely up to you.
[HOTARO]
Damn it, Sis.
You really better not have
just laid a bunch of work
down on my feet again.
[BOTH gasp]
[ERU]
Oh, excuse me!
Pardon, but are you Yoshino, the
Broadcasting Club's president?
Yeah, that's right.
Who are you?
[ERU]
Nice to meet you.
I am so glad you
were actually here!
I'm Eru Chitanda--
[YOSHINO] You're the
Classic Lit Club president!
The timing couldn't be better!
I was literally just
on my way to see you!
Would you like to be a guest
on our radio show today
during lunch?
I think interviewing
the president of the club
that's sure to be Jumoji's final
target would be a huge hit.
Well?
[ERU] I couldn't have
planned it better myself!
[ERU] I would be honored
to be a guest on your show!
Great!
We meet at 12 noon
in the studio!
The broadcast starts
at 12:30 sharp.
See you then!
Right!
Hey, guys. I'm back.
Great! Hi, Chitanda.
Thanks for watching the store.
Have there been any
further developments?
The thief skipped "ku."
He stole gen , a string
from the Light Music Club.
I think we should
start over from scratch.
[ERU]
What's your opinion, Oreki?
He's all engrossed
with that doujin manga;
he's had his head
buried in it for a while.
[ERU]
Oh.
This is so good.
Oh, yeah?
Hold on...
What's the matter?
[ERU] For some reason,
that picture looks really
familiar to me.
[HOTARO] Your eyes are
playing tricks on you.
My sister just
brought this to me.
No way.
There's no doubt in my mind.
Chitanda, this is really
not the time for that stuff.
But... I've seen it.
I... I have to know!
[HOTARO]
There it is.
It's on the tip of my tongue!
Swallow it.
But I can't!
That's not my problem.
Just let me look at
another page, okay?
Fine, then.
Thanks, I won't take long!
[SATOSHI giggling]
This one!
It looks similar to
a poster I saw outside
of the conference room!
[SATOSHI]
Yeah, you're right. It does.
Hey, Oreki.
Would you mind letting
me borrow this manga?
I want to compare the two!
All right.
Just make sure you
bring it back quickly.
I kind of need it.
[ERU]
Right!
This is some fine
artwork right here.
Thank you. Have a lovely day!
[MAYAKA]
I'm all done.
Now what?
[STUDENTS chattering]
Great.
[chattering continues]
[SAWAI]
Whoop-sies!
[SAWAI gasps]
[water splashes]
I'm so sorry, Ibara.
I really didn't mean to do that.
[MAYAKA]
It's no big deal.
It's khaki, so even if it
stains, it won't show up anyway.
At least I hope not.
Ibara...
[MAYAKA]
Sorry, President.
I hope you can
manage without me.
[YUASA] You need to change out
of your rainbow parakeet
costume, though.
[MAYAKA]
Don't worry about me! I'm fine.
Oh, Mayaka!
Hi, Chi.
Hey, are you busy right now?
Gym clothes?
Mm-hmm. I had to change.
No, I'm not busy, what's up?
Oh. It's about this!
What? That's crazy!
Where did you get it?
I borrowed it from Oreki.
He was reading it earlier.
Why did he have it?
He said that his sister
brought it to him.
Mayaka, how familiar are you
with this particular manga?
Well... very. Oddly enough.
[ERU]
That's awesome!
I saw a poster promoting
the Cultural Festival,
and I'm certain that
whoever drew this manga
also drew the poster!
I think the style's identical,
but I need an expert opinion!
I have to know!
[MAYAKA]
Where did you see this poster?
[ERU]
Next to the conference room!
[MAYAKA]
Right! Let's go!
[ERU]
What do you think?
I'm 99% sure it's
the same person.
The way they handle
the ears is unmistakable.
So I was correct!
Thanks, I'm glad to hear it!
It was lucky that
I ran into you!
[laughs]
You had to know!
Yep!
Well, then.
Would you like to
find out who drew it?
Yeah, of course! Bonus points!
[TANABE]
Yes?
We meet again, Tanabe.
Hello. You're from the...
hold on.
Classic Lit Club.
That's right.
So, how can I help you?
We're really sorry
to bother you,
but we're curious: Could you
tell us who drew that poster
on the wall right there?
Ah. That would be Kugayama.
[ERU] What?
You mean Muneyoshi Kugayama?
The student council president?
The same.
I had to badger him a bit to
convince him, but he caved.
Turned out well, huh?
Yes!
It's absolutely beautiful!
A masterpiece!
[TANABE laughs] He'll be tickled
when I tell him you said that.
[MAYAKA]
This is incredible!
I now know the author
and the artist!
Maybe I'll get the chance to
chat with them in person!
I hope this lucky
streak keeps rolling.
[ERU]
We solved the mystery!
So, was it the same person?
Wait... What the heck?
Why the gym clothes?
What about Manga Club?
Oh. I had to change.
It was the same person!
We even found out his name!
Oh, wow. Good for you.
[ERU]
It was Muneyoshi Kugayama.
Isn't that a surprise?
Should I know who that is?
All right. Come on, Hotaro,
that's enough messing
around for today.
[HOTARO]
Seriously, who is that?
[MAYAKA]
The student council president.
Right. I remember.
[HOTARO] This whole time
I thought it was pronounced
"Rikuyama."
So that means this
Kugayama guy is the artist
of the Anshinin Takuha group who
created that manga?
[SATOSHI] What do you mean,
"Anshinin Takuha?"
That's meant to be
read as, "Ajimu."
It's a place in Kyushu.
Is that information crucial
to surviving my daily life?
[ERU]
I mean...
The pronunciation is
written in Romanized text
right here on the cover,
next to the name.
Kugayama did the artwork,
but the story itself was written
by someone named Anjo Haruna.
[HOTARO] Oh. So you know
something about this manga?
It's one of my favorites.
I bought it at last year's
cultural festival.
[HOTARO] For Ibara to say that
openly, it must be remarkable.
[MAYAKA]
Listen, Oreki...
Do you think... I could
borrow it for a bit?
Yeah, that's cool,
but give me a little while.
I need it right now.
You do?
Oh, yeah! I almost forgot!
The Broadcasting Club
is having me as a guest
on their lunchtime show!
[HOTARO]
She's what?!
[MAYAKA]
Wow, Chi, that's amazing!
[SATOSHI]
Way to go!
We couldn't have
asked for better.
Our goal of selling all these
copies just got within reach!
Now, let me coach
you through the basics
of giving a good interview.
[ERU]
Would you really do that?
[SATOSHI]
Yes.
First and foremost, guests are
only allotted five minutes.
That's a mere blip.
So the question becomes:
"How can you manage to
stand out with so little time?"
[HOTARO]
Getting Around at Kanyasai .
Gardening Club .
Cooking Club .
The Light Music Club .
One of Christie's
most famous works.
The Kudryavka Sequence .
What's up?
How 'bout it?
'Bout what?
Nothing.
[HOTARO]
Oh, well.
My thoughts were at a
standstill, anyway.
Normally, I would
try to get unstuck
by talking everything out
with these guys.
But Chitanda would
stand in my way.
If she knew what
I was trying to do,
she'd definitely be against it.
[HOTARO]
Satoshi.
[SATOSHI]
Hm?
I need to borrow you
for a second.
You've figured something out,
haven't you, Hotaro?
[gasps]
Hey, is that true?
Tell us, Oreki!
[HOTARO] No one asked you to
share your hunches!
Now Chitanda's got that
insatiably curious look
in her eyes!
[ERU] Have you had some
kind of realization?
No, I haven't.
I promise you!
So, then,
are you saying this isn't about
the Jumoji matter at all?
Well, uh...
Come on. Out with it.
[ERU]
Yes, please tell us.
I'm curious, and I want to
be in the loop about things.
So why keep it a secret?
[HOTARO]
Not fair! Okay, fine.
[HOTARO] It does have to do
with the Jumoji affair.
Great! Then you have to tell us!
It's obscene. That's why
I left you out of it. Okay?
[SATOSHI laughing]
So... it's "obscene," huh?
Let's hear this lewdness.
Sorry to drag you
out here with this.
No worries.
Doesn't bother me at all.
[HOTARO] It's not even
like I have anything
earth-shattering to talk about.
I just have a few
problems I can't seem
to wrap my head around,
and I have a feeling that they
might be pretty significant.
Did you discover
some hidden link
between the clubs that have
already fallen victim?
[HOTARO] No. I haven't
discovered anything there.
Then, did you find some
mistake in Jumoji's methods
that might lead us to an answer?
[HOTARO]
It's not so much that, either.
What's wrong?
[SATOSHI]
How do we proceed?
There are over a
thousand suspects.
How are we ever supposed
to identify the culprit
without finding any
real leads or mistakes?
Yeah. Good question.
[SATOSHI]
But it's not possible!
Look, it's not like I don't
have any ideas about it.
I just need to gather my
thoughts a little better.
Mm-hmm. Let's hear them, then.
I'm looking forward
to it, Hotaro.
First of all...
What's the evidence that he's
stealing ten specific items
from ten different clubs?
We just assumed that because of
the way he signed his notes.
[SATOSHI] And that assumption
has since been challenged
by new events.
[HOTARO]
Second...
Why does he leave a calling
card at all of his crimes?
[SATOSHI]
Yeah.
You mean like this?
Third question...
Why does he keep saying that the
missing items have been lost?
Wouldn't you say
"stolen," or, "taken?"
Fourth, why does he always leave
a Kanyasai guidebook, too?
It's not the only thing
that lists all the clubs.
Why choose that in particular?
That reminds me.
I picked this up.
It was at the
Cooking Club event.
Fifth, why'd he choose
to target the Cooking Club
and the Gardening Club?
There are several other clubs
that start with "E" and "O."
Especially since the Cooking
Club's usually called
the Ryori Club, not Oryori .
Answering that could
help us figure out
whether the Classic Lit Club
or the Industrial Arts Club
will be hit next.
Sixth question, and no
doubt the weirdest one of all:
Why did he decide to
skip over "ku,"
and hit "ke" next instead?
[SATOSHI] That's simple: he did
it to keep from being noticed.
The Global Action Club
was crawling with civilians,
and it would've made
the crime too difficult.
[HOTARO]
Lastly, seventh.
There's this.
Are you implying the manga has
something to do with this case?
[HOTARO] That's my hunch,
but I haven't decided yet.
What do you think when you hear,
"one of Christie's
most famous works?"
[SATOSHI]
Let me see...
I'd say,
And Then There Were None ,
Then Murder on
the Orient Express ,
A.B.C. Murders ,
and The Murder
of Roger Ackroyd .
Those come to mind.
[HOTARO] If someone were to use
one of them
as the basis for a manga
with the title
The Kudryavka Sequence ,
I'd think they would use, The
A.B.C. Murders , wouldn't you?
[SATOSHI] Well, Kudryavka
was a nickname for the dog
the Soviets shot into space,
but she never made it back.
With that violent image in mind,
I think I would say,
And Then There Were None ,
instead.
[HOTARO] Well, since
we're only speculating,
we don't have to
pin it down just yet.
[sighs]
I believe I'm finally
beginning to piece together
what you're getting at, Hotaro.
Satoshi,
do you know if there's a manga
called, The Kudryavka Sequence
being sold at the festival?
There's not.
At least, the executive
committee hasn't been told.
I also think Mayaka would have
mentioned it to us
if the Manga Club
was selling it.
Keyword, "if."
A Corpse by Evening
came out at last year's
Cultural Festival, apparently.
In the afterword,
there was an announcement
that they would write
a manga this year
that was going to be
a take on one of
"Christie's most famous works."
You and I have said we
think that work is either
And Then There Were None ,
or The A.B.C. Murders .
At this year's
Cultural Festival,
events similar to The A.B.C.
Murders are taking place,
albeit on a much
less sinister scale.
Is that just coincidence?
In other words, you think the
key to solving the Jumoji case
is contained in the end of
" A Corpse by Evening ."
Is that what you're saying?
[HOTARO] I guess I'm saying
I don't think they're
completely unrelated.
[SATOSHI]
Hmm...
[HOTARO] I think this Jumoji
character is just trying
to carry on with his little
caper for as long as he can,
causing an uproar
at the festival
with as little
interference as possible.
I don't think this
is all just for fun.
Still, why would he
skip over "ku?"
There are a number of ways
to pull that one off.
Satoshi, there's a specific
reason he's doing this.
I'm gonna head back in.
I wanna help
Chitanda prepare.
Yeah, okay. Go ahead.
I'm going to see if there's
anything in this stuff
you gave me.
Oh! Satoshi!
Tell Chitanda to have
some "ko" items
out somewhere they'd
be easy to find.
Right. Bait...
I like that idea.
Proofed manuscripts?
Koryogenko fits the bill.
[SATOSHI] I have high hopes
for this, Hotaro.
We go live when he
gives us the cue, okay?
Right!
On in five seconds.
Four. Three.
A special broadcast of
Yasukuni Yoshino's Radio Beat!
Hi, hello there.
I'm your favorite DJ,
Yasukuni Yoshino.
With me on this, the last day
of the Cultural Festival,
is Classic Lit Club president,
Eru Chitanda!
Oh... right! Me!
I'm so happy to be
here talking to you!
[MAYAKA] Next time: "The
Kudryavka Sequence."