[WAITRESS 10A]
Please enjoy!
[IRISU]
Is something wrong?
Uh-- No.
When you asked me if I
wanted to have tea with you,
I didn't know you
were being literal.
Don't worry. I'll get the tab.
Oh.
[IRISU] Nakajo's theory
didn't pan out, then?
Nor Haba's?
Right.
Neither did Sawakiguchi's?
No, I don't believe hers did.
[sighs] I see.
I'm sorry to disappoint.
[IRISU] You don't have
to be nice about it.
[gasps]
[IRISU]
I'm incredibly curious.
What was so wrong
about their theories?
Well, first,
let's talk about
Nakajo's hypothesis.
You see? That's why
Sawakiguchi's theory
doesn't hold up
to scrutiny, either.
Indeed.
Which member of your group
turned down Nakajo's idea, then?
That'd be me.
As well as Haba and
Sawakiguchi's ideas?
Yeah, that's right.
When I first approached you
about this, you told me
I shouldn't expect
too much from you.
I guess our standards
of expectation differ.
Because you proceeded
to disprove the theories
our detectives put forth.
But to be honest,
that was my expectation.
You knew I'd disprove them?
[IRISU] I never thought they'd
be up to the challenge.
I was right.
None of them possesses the level
of deductive reasoning skills
necessary to tackle
something like this.
You mean the whole
detective thing was a ruse?
Of course.
I'm not calling
them incompetent.
They have their own
strengths, to be sure.
But that doesn't make
them useful to me
in a situation like this, and I
had to interest you somehow.
Why not just--
If it weren't for you.
If it weren't for you,
we would have gone with
one of their ideas,
and the whole production
would have ended in failure.
And I refuse to have my name
attached to anything
that isn't a success.
Man, that's pretty cold.
You're heartless, aren't you?
If I must be cruel in order
to get the best product,
so be it. I will do
whatever it takes.
I had heard from
three different people
that only you could fix this.
Eru Chitanda said it,
as well as someone from
outside our school.
Masashi Togaito championed
your prowess, too.
When I learned of your
reputation, I was convinced
you had to be our detective
and save our film.
There was no doubt in my mind.
I was after you from
the very beginning.
Not the Classic Lit Club.
So, Oreki.
After carefully weighing
all the rumors about you
against your own assessment
of the detectives' theories,
I have decided.
It's all true.
You are special.
[HOTARO gasps]
[IRISU]
You're gifted. A true genius.
So I'll ask again:
will you help us?
Say yes.
You are the only person who
can save our class project.
I couldn't bear it
if all that hard work
went to waste.
I'm really not a genius.
I just... get lucky
from time to time.
That's a real shame.
Let me tell you a little story.
It might change your
perspective a bit.
Once, there was a sports
team with a benchwarmer.
[IRISU] The benchwarmer did
her very best to get herself
off the bench
and onto the field,
but all her efforts
were in vain.
Try as she might,
her hard work was no match
for the athletic ability
of the other team members.
There was one
player in particular
whose natural talent
was undeniable.
Compared to our benchwarmer,
the difference was
like night and day.
At one match, the
talented girl performed
exceptionally well, even for
her, and was named the MVP.
Interviewers flocked to
her, hungry for a quote.
One said, "You're amazing!
We're dying to
know your secrets!"
She answered humbly.
"Secrets?
Oh, no, I just got lucky!"
[HOTARO grumbles]
I believe the poor
benchwarmer took great offense
upon hearing such
an inconsiderate remark.
Do you?
It's not wrong to acknowledge
who you really are.
If you don't,
you make fools out of
those who praise you.
[HOTARO]
Is she right? Am I special?
[HOTARO] Do I deny myself
credit for being who I am?
If so, then why?
Do I think it's wrong
to believe in my talent?
[HOTARO gasps]
[exhales]
All right, Irisu.
My answer--
[SATOSHI] You're going to
school of your own accord
during summer vacation?
Are pigs flying?
Do you have to?
No, but am I not
allowed to go to school
if I want to?
You are.
It's just not like
you, that's all.
I'm fulfilling a personal
request from Irisu.
I'm going to solve the
murder in Class 2-F's film.
What? No way! Who are you?
I am Hotaro Oreki, the
hard-working teenage detective.
Did you say "hard-working"?
This is spooky.
[HOTARO]
Hmph.
Seriously, I never thought
I would see the day.
Are you doing this
because of Chitanda again?
No.
Then, what's your motivation?
"If I don't have to,
I'm not going to," remember?
That is your motto.
Am I correct?
[HOTARO]
Satoshi.
[SATOSHI]
Hm?
Ah--
Please be honest.
Do you believe that there's
anything which only you can do?
No way.
Really?
Don't you remember?
I don't have any
special talents.
Here, check it out.
I think of myself
as a Sherlockian.
But I know deep down that
I couldn't really be one.
I don't have the kind of
iron-clad constitution
that could handle
diving headlong
into the murky depths
of obscure knowledge.
I'm nothing but an impostor.
If Mayaka suddenly took
a serious interest
in Sherlock Holmes,
I guarantee this: She'd surpass
me in three months, flat.
I'm a jack of all trades,
but a master of none.
I'm a serious dabbler,
that's all.
I get my passport stamped
and I go on my way.
I'm an expert at nothing,
but that's all right.
But, I get it.
Irisu roped you
into this somehow.
[HOTARO grumbles]
Even so, you still
doubt your aptitude.
Which is normal, I suppose.
Don't you have any
doubts about yourself?
Even a little?
I don't. I know I'm average.
Let's go.
Mayaka is probably
at school already.
I wanna say hi.
Satoshi!
[SATOSHI]
Hm?
What I think may not matter,
one way or the other,
but, in my opinion, you're
way better than just average.
If you wanted to be
a Sherlockian someday,
I believe that you would
be one of the finest
Japan had to offer.
There are about a million things
I'd rather aspire to
than being a Sherlockian.
Though I've gotta admit...
[gasps]
[SATOSHI]
I couldn't envy you more.
Just so you know.
[MAYAKA]
What?!
It's summer vacation and Oreki
still came to school
of his own accord?
You got a problem with that?
[MAYAKA]
It's creepy.
I'm sure it foretells some
kind of apocalyptic disaster.
Look, I decided to
help solve the mystery.
Seriously? How come?
He, he.
I bet Irisu seduced you
into it somehow, didn't she?
[HOTARO grunts]
You nailed it. Sharp as a tack!
Whatever.
Enough about me, what happened
after you left yesterday?
You mean with Chi?
Well, I know she made
it home all right.
But when I called
her this morning,
she was in bed with a hangover.
That's funny.
And all from those chocolates.
Ahem.
Well, anyway.
I think it would help if
we watched the movie again.
[SUGIMURA]
Kaito!
Th-There's blood everywhere!
[fake screams]
[YAMANISHI]
Oh, no. What is that?
[MAYAKA]
Wow, Kaito's severed arm
looks so lifelike in that shot.
I'd swear that it was real!
I think the prop team
is the most talented
part of this entire production.
[KATSUTA]
Oh, no.
It sure doesn't seem
like a very complicated
set-up from my perspective.
That's true.
They did an excellent job
of making it look simple, huh?
No, they didn't.
The reason the setting
looks so simple
doesn't have anything to do
with the filmmakers at all.
[HOTARO]
What, then?
Here's my assessment:
Anything good in this film
is a complete accident.
They don't know
what they are doing,
so the mystery
ends up falling flat.
[HOTARO]
Damn.
[NARRATOR 8A]
These students from Class 2-F
have decided to participate
in the Kanyasai.
[SATOSHI]
You're right.
The first time I saw it,
I assumed at this point
it was a regular documentary,
not a murder mystery.
The production values are
extremely weak, overall.
Like, which part?
The camerawork, for starters.
Yeah, I agree.
Okay.
How would you shoot it, Ibara?
Well, I'm glad you asked.
Let's see. Where was it?
Hold on. Right here.
Wouldn't it be better to
use a wide shot here?
Just to give some perspective
on the size of the room
and how small the
characters are in it?
Good point.
And, also...
This part.
Hey, Sugimura!
What did you find up there?
[SUGIMURA]
Well, it's pretty clean, mostly.
The rooms in this wing...
[MAYAKA] I think it would
be smarter to shoot
from Sugimura's perspective,
so the audience could see
that the lobby's in
full view from up there.
If the viewers only see
him from down there,
there's no way they would
be able to tell that.
Okay.
What else is there?
You know...
How 'bout we not?
What, how come?
You'll never stop.
[MAYAKA growls]
Plus, criticizing the camerawork
won't solve the mystery.
Now, now.
There might be some
value in criticism.
[YAMAUCHI]
There you are! Finally!
Uh-- Ah, ha...
So this is where
you've been hiding!
Yamauchi! How's it going?
Whoa!
Hey, man, no need
to resort to violence!
[YAMAUCHI]
It's for your own good!
You should be thanking me!
Come on!
I've got a ton of other
things to do today!
Dummy! Omichi's gonna shred you!
Don't you even care
if you fail the class?
Go with him.
You do need those
remedial lessons.
No!
Solving Hongo's mystery is
just as important as math!
Come on, Hotaro, just pull
the answer out of thin air!
[YAMAUCHI] What are you even
talkin' about, you moron?
Oh, it's fascinating--
[grunts]
No! Let me stay!
I have to know the
answer! The answer!
He put up a good fight.
What is wrong with that boy?
[footsteps]
[MAYAKA]
He's not giving up!
[SATOSHI]
I'm sorry, my friends.
I'm a slave to circumstances
beyond my control.
Though it's come to this.
[YAMAUCHI]
Fukube!
[SATOSHI] Think of this notebook
as me and I shall be with you.
Stand up! Let's go!
Okay! I'm coming. Don't drag me!
[HOTARO]
Ridiculous.
Well then,
I guess I'd better go, too.
Really?
Don't give me that look.
Helping Irisu is one thing,
but I'm making no sacrifices
for the likes of you.
Oh, yeah?
Such attitude.
I have library duty today.
If you'd told me before,
I could have cancelled it.
It's your own fault for
springing this on us.
That said...
I'm sorry. I mean it.
Okay.
Let's split up and
explore the building!
Hey!
Damn it! He's dead!
[SUGIMURA]
Th-There's blood everywhere!
[KONOSU]
There has to be a set of keys
lying around this
place somewhere.
[fake screams]
[CLASS 2-F STUDENTS murmuring]
I've got it.
So, that's it.
That's what she intended.
[knocking]
[HOTARO]
Come in.
First, I have to know.
Did you figure it out?
Okay. Then let me hear it.
[HOTARO]
Right.
It goes without saying
that the locked
room is key here.
No pun intended.
At the time he died--I mean--
at the point in which he
was murdered in the movie,
none of the others could have
entered or left that room
without being noticed.
There's nothing to be
nervous about here.
Uh--
The stage left wing
was also locked.
Damn it! He's dead!
[HOTARO] The window, which
is the only other way out,
is difficult to open.
That means it's not
possible for the killer
to have come or gone by
any way except the door.
So how'd they get in the room?
I can't tell from the
video if there's some rig
built into the door
that springs the lock.
So it's safe to assume
that the killer
used the master key
to let themselves in.
However, Sugimura was
able to see the lobby.
Because of Sugimura,
no one could have entered
the stage right hallway, which
creates a second locked room.
They couldn't have
gotten the master key
from out of the office
and gone down that hall
without going through the lobby.
He'd spot them.
So what possible
explanations does that leave?
If none of the six
could have done it
without being seen,
there's just one answer.
A seventh character must
have committed the murder.
Interesting.
Sawakiguchi said that.
Yes.
When she first
brought it up to us,
I thought it was ridiculous,
and I wrote it off completely.
It didn't seem like
a viable option.
But then she said that
Hongo was trying to cast
a seventh character.
Remembering that piece is
what ultimately convinced me.
But...
Hongo had written the
rest of the film's script
to be pretty straightforward.
It seemed unlikely
that she'd introduce
a new character at that point.
However,
we noticed a few odd occurrences
at other points in the film.
Satoshi pointed them out
for me in his notes.
"Konosu finds the floorplan.
It seems illuminated.
I think it's lit
by a flashlight."
"I saw it again.
In the part where they
go looking for Kaito."
"The hall is pitch black.
Can't see a thing.
Suddenly, a flashlight, again."
What's weird about a flashlight?
Nothing.
Except that none of the six
kids is ever seen holding one
at any other point
in the whole movie.
If you look closely
at the scene
where they discover
Kaito's body,
immediately after the
illumination in the hallway,
you can clearly see that
no one has a flashlight.
There was enough time
for them to have hidden it,
but why would they do that?
There's no good reason to.
I know, I know.
You assumed it's scene lighting,
but hold that thought.
Just keep everything I
said about the flashlight
in mind for later.
There's something else.
And don't get offended.
Know it's coming from
a true film buff.
She complains that
the movie is boring.
And it's poorly produced.
The camerawork in particular
lacked any innovation or skill.
But what if that
was intentional?
A clue for the viewers?
How was it shot?
The camera appears
to be in the same place
as the other six
for the whole movie.
Well, then,
it seems like you've
figured it out.
I think I have.
Do you mean...
...that the cameraman
is the seventh character
and the killer?
[HOTARO]
Mm-hm.
There were seven characters
from the beginning of the film.
The six that you see
on screen the entire time,
and the person behind
the camera shooting.
That makes seven.
Now, watch closely.
In some of the scenes,
the actors seem
to be aware of the camera.
They pay subtle
attention to him.
They look at him occasionally,
though not very much.
Calling him the
cameraman is confusing.
Let's rename him
the seventh man.
Now remember the flashlight.
It wouldn't be odd for him
to be carrying one,
if it's his job to
chronicle the experience.
The poor quality of the
camera work, and the fact
that none of the
scenes were shot
from multiple angles
makes sense.
If the guy behind the
camera is a character
in the story, that's expected.
Also--
and this part is
really important--
When the characters
split up to look around,
the camera stayed in the lobby
after all six of
the others had left.
There's that weird,
empty moment,
and the scene fades out.
So check it out.
After the others were
gone, the seventh man
stopped filming for
a few minutes, left.
Came back, started rolling,
and waited for them.
And so, it was a
really simple crime.
The seventh man made
sure they were gone,
stopped his camera,
and ran to the office
to get the master key.
Then, while the others
were busy elsewhere,
he found Kaito and killed him.
After he committed the murder,
he used the master key
to lock the room behind him.
Then he returned quickly to the
lobby and waited for the others.
That is the conclusion I drew.
If Hongo hadn't already
cast a seventh actor,
then I suggest you try to
find one as soon as possible.
Two questions.
First, if your theory is true,
the fact that no one
ever talks to the seventh man
or acknowledges him much
seems a little
awkward, doesn't it?
Maybe Hongo was
using that as a way
to establish a motive.
The seventh man
could be an outcast,
someone that others
usually ignore.
As a result, he never felt
confident speaking up
when they were around,
hence his silence.
Next question.
If your hypothesis is correct,
wouldn't the other characters
figure it out eventually,
the same as you did?
They would all suspect
the seventh man
because he'd stayed
in the lobby.
Also, the "second locked
room" part of your theory
is still intact.
His exit from the lobby and
his return after the murder
would have been in public
view the whole time.
In which case,
everyone would know
who the murderer
was immediately.
[HOTARO chuckles]
[gasps]
[HOTARO] I don't mean to be
rude when I say this, but,
what does it matter?
Like, who cares?
[gasps]
It's not important
whether the characters
know who the killer is or not.
As long as the audience is
intrigued by the mystery,
don't you think
that's the point here?
That may be the reason
the film doesn't have
a detective character
in the first place.
The movie doesn't deal
with the people in the story
figuring it out.
They know who among them
would be the killer.
[IRISU]
Congratulations.
Huh?
I believe that you have just
solved Hongo's mystery.
It's an astoundingly
bold approach.
That's for certain, but it
corresponds to all of the facts,
so I can't imagine there's
any legitimate reason
to dispute it.
Anyway, thank you.
Now we can resume
our production.
[gasps]
I guess my
assumption about you
has proven correct after all.
You do have formidable skill.
The power no one else possesses.
Uh, thank you.
That's nice to hear.
I'm very flattered.
I mean it.
So, what do you think the
title of our film should be?
Oh, the title?
Off the top of your head.
I'm sure everyone will approve,
and I know I would like
anything you dream up.
Huh.
Well, let me think.
In light of the culprit...
How do you feel about,
A Blind Spot to All ?
[IRISU chuckles]
That's a good idea.
I think it's the one.
[HOTARO]
Home run.
[GIRL 10A]
Good morning!
[TEACHER 10A]
All the third years,
please listen up.
[PRINCIPAL] It's October,
time for everyone's favorite:
the cultural festival!
It's strange.
How could anyone have
gotten into that room
without us seeing?
[KATSUTA]
I don't know. But I think...
...there's one person
who could've.
Did you murder Kaito?
You did it, didn't you?
[SENOUE]
Murderer!
[KATSUTA]
You're gonna pay for this!
Turned out great, huh?
[KATSUTA]
You can't run away from this!
[gasps]
[NAKAJO]
He pulled it off, didn't he?
[KAITO]
Man, I gotta tell ya,
I was amazed by
that surprise ending!
[HOTARO]
It's the real-life Kaito!
[NAKAJO]
Hey, you're the guy!
Everybody's saying
you're the mastermind
behind the whole thing.
Yeah. Sure.
Man, that ending
was genius, kid!
Sure surprised me!
Hey! It's The Great Detective!
"Great detective"?
Yeah! Good work!
Though, I have to say, it's sad
that when the seventh
character is revealed
to be the killer, the
others turn violent, too.
They should have
just turned him in.
Yeah.
Well, anyway, thanks
for everything.
See ya!
Cool.
Listen, Nakajo...
What's up?
[SAWAKIGUCHI] Your pit stains
are out of control.
That arm was worth all
the work we put into it.
Tch.
[HOTARO] I guess Haba wasn't
satisfied with the ending.
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro!
Huh?
[SATOSHI]
We saw the film.
[HOTARO]
What did you think?
It's pretty good.
[gasps]
It was very interesting.
Who would've have pinned
it on the cameraman?
The other day when we met.
Had you already
figured it all out?
No, at that point,
I hadn't quite
come up with it yet.
Really.
Huh?
[HOTARO]
Weird.
She doesn't seem
surprised at all.
Then again, it is Mayaka.
What'd I expect?
Hey, Oreki.
[HOTARO]
Hm? Yeah?
Listen.
I-I thought...
I'll tell you later.
Well, you did a great job,
as usual, my friend.
And as for the
Empress. She's happy.
Plus the audience loved
the element of surprise
with the seventh man at the end.
[MAYAKA]
Oreki...
There's something I have to ask.
What's that?
What are you doing?
Now you're solely responsible
for that ending, aren't you?
[HOTARO]
That's right.
All of it?
Mostly.
[MAYAKA]
Hm...
Then how do you account
for what Haba said
when we met with the detectives?
Haba?
[gasps] It's just...
They didn't use a rope
anywhere in that movie,
and Hongo specifically
asked him for one.
[gasps]
[HOTARO] Next time:
"Credit Roll of Fools."