[TEACHER 6A] So that's when
it all changed for Rome.
When the Romans
overthrew the Etruscans
in 509 B.C.,
Rome established a republic.
The people were divided
into two classes:
The patricians,
made up of aristocrats,
and the plebeians,
made up of common folk...
[HOTARO]
I'm so bored.
[TEACHER 6A] The classes
were strictly forbidden
from intermixing.
Now, the aristocrats
held all important
governmental offices,
such as the two consuls,
and the 300 senators.
Furthermore, the senate
was considered to be
the highest legislative
and advisory body,
meeting in the curia
to convene and pass laws.
[MITSUISHI]
Did you hear that?
[GIRL 6A]
Yeah, what was it?
Is that Class A?
With Mr. Omichi?
Yeah, I think so.
[OMICHI] It's as if you have no
desire to learn anything,
so why are you even here?!
It is Class A.
What the heck's going on?
Sounds like Omichi snapped
and is on one of
his tirades again.
[OMICHI] Hurry up,
we don't have all day!
--What's your answer?!
--[ERU] Mr. Omichi...
Maybe you should look
at the lesson plan again.
I think you've got it wrong.
[OMICHI]
Excuse me?!
[ERU] Before you scream at us,
you ought to be sure
you're not the one
making a mistake.
[HOTARO]
Is that Chitanda?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[OMICHI] Ah, sorry.
I see where we are.
Tamura, you may sit down.
[TEACHER 6A]
Okay!
Let's get back to
the Roman Republic.
Let's see, where were we?
Oh, yes, the senate
and the curia.
So the curia was a huge
building on the grounds
of the Roman forum.
[MAYAKA] It was your idea
for us to get together
in the first place, Fukube!
Hey, Mayaka.
Why don't you just
try to calm down?
You should just
stay out of this, Chi.
Look, maybe you
did have a reason,
but it's common
courtesy to call!
Or you could have
even sent me a text
at the very least!
I wouldn't have cared
if you'd cancelled,
but to stand me up
without a word?
I know you've
got a cell phone,
so why didn't you use it?
It never occurs to you
to do the right thing!
You don't care about
anyone but yourself,
and that's the truth!
[HOTARO] That's a bold move
on your part, Chitanda.
[MAYAKA] Apologizing won't let
you off the hook this time!
You're full of
useless information...
[HOTARO]
Your efforts are futile, though.
You had to know
how mad I would be,
but you didn't care!
Then it started
storming like crazy!
Rain, thunder, lighting,
hail! Hail, Fukube!
You're the most inconsiderate
person I've ever met!
I even got all dressed up,
like an idiot,
and by the time I got home,
my favorite outfit was ruined!
--Ruined, Fukube!
--[HOTARO] Aren't you tired yet?
Yes, I am.
Why don't you
take a breather?
[MAYAKA]
Fine, good idea.
[HOTARO] I didn't intervene
for your sake, dummy.
Wow.
I've gotta say,
you get mad really often.
Does yelling make
you feel any better?
You know, I only seem
to get ticked enough
to yell when you are involved,
which I think is pretty telling.
Yeah, makes sense.
You know, maybe you
should take a few pages
from Chitanda's book.
She never gets riled up
about anything.
Huh?
I've never seen you
like that, either, Satoshi.
And come to think of it,
though I've seen
him get annoyed,
Oreki doesn't often
get downright angry.
Not as far as I have
noticed, anyway.
Fuku totally gets angry.
Yeah, I've seen him livid.
[ERU]
Do you really?
Of course.
I may not flip out and start
screaming like Mayaka.
But yeah, I get mad.
I couldn't even
imagine you having
that kind of reaction
about anything.
[SATOSHI]
Well, I am human, after all.
I get angry sometimes.
[HOTARO] True, but you
don't make a big production
about venting your feelings
in front of everyone.
He's not very scary when
he gets angry, though.
Are you serious?
Well, it's sure news to me.
That piques my curiosity.
I want to see it.
[SATOSHI]
What?
[HOTARO] I predict that Chitanda
will hatch some grand scheme
to trick Satoshi into
getting ticked off.
Just to see if it's possible.
I can't wait for that.
Oreki, do you have
a secret temper?
There's no hot
blood in that one at all.
Because he's
so level headed?
It's more that he
is way too selfish
and shallow to get upset
about anything in life.
[HOTARO]
Hey, we may be frenemies,
but that's over the line.
Whoa, I got mad!
Don't get me
started on Hotaro;
we'll be here all night.
But Chitanda's lack of
irascibility is almost heroic.
She's like a Zen master.
Her patience is incredible.
No matter what, she
always rolls with the punches.
You might be happier if you
tried to be more like her.
That's easy for you to say,
but you don't understand
what it's like to be me.
I don't think I could
ever be a calm as Chi.
Hold on. I'm confused.
Is all this a compliment?
For sure.
It's totally a good thing.
It's just an observation.
There's no judgement either way.
Definitely.
Not being able to
get angry is not good,
but the ability to rise
above it is another story.
After all, wrath is
a pretty serious sin.
You should cut me
some slack, Mayaka.
The way you
lash out isn't right.
A sin?
You mean the
seven deadly sins?
Yeah! I'm impressed, Chitanda.
They're pretty well known
throughout the world.
Hey, Mayaka, have you
ever heard of them?
Yeah. Everybody knows
about those, right?
Wait a sec, I thought
there were 108 sins.
No, those are
Earthly Desires.
Excuse me.
Let me see...
There's wrath, pride,
gluttony, greed.
Envy, lust, and sloth
are the three others.
Yeah, that's right!
Sloth, you say?
[HOTARO]
What's she looking at me for?
Wow! That means Chi is perfect!
You're honest, kind,
and you don't eat too much.
I wouldn't go that far.
I doubt that you've
ever been greedy,
and you're really diligent.
I am?
And another thing...
As for lust, you're not slutty.
Awkward...
There's no way to
know if she's envious,
but I would bet she isn't.
[HOTARO] This has turned from
giving her simple compliments
into full-out teasing.
[ERU]
Let's stop talking about it!
Anyway, when I am hungry,
I can eat more food than
you would ever imagine!
[HOTARO]
No surprise there.
I think her new nickname
should be Saint Chi!
Eru Chitanda kind of sounds like
an angel's name, doesn't it?
The Archangels Michael,
Gabriel, Uriel, and Eru!
[laughing]
I don't think this is funny!
She got mad.
You're right. She yelled at us.
Sorry, we didn't mean it, Chi.
[ERU]
I'm done talking.
Good job!
You know exactly what to
say to make a girl angry!
Hold on just a minute!
I think she's mad at you, too!
[ERU] Just 'cause wrath
is a sin doesn't mean
it's good to never get angry.
The same goes for the other
deadly sins, too, doesn't it?
Pride and greed can be useful
as long as they're
kept in balance.
What do you mean?
Well, imagine a person who
has no pride whatsoever.
Doesn't that mean they
also have zero confidence?
And if a person doesn't have
an ounce of greed at all,
wouldn't it be difficult
for them to take care
of themselves or a family?
And think about envy.
If people didn't ever feel it,
there wouldn't be
as many innovations,
new technologies or ideas.
Oh! Um...
I didn't mean to go into lecture
mode or anything, sorry.
Hmm... That's okay.
Interesting take.
[HOTARO]
So they're fine in moderation?
I just don't think it's wise
to take the term "deadly sins"
so literally, and then
live our lives as if
those seven
normal human emotions
are gonna kill us or something.
So then what you're saying is
that it's not necessarily
a bad thing to get mad?
Yeah, pretty much.
I mean, if you always
stifle your anger,
it might start to get
in the way of your ability
to enjoy your life, too.
[HOTARO]
I definitely get mad.
But, like, if that's
your philosophy,
then why don't you ever get mad?
Because it's draining.
And I avoid doing
things that wear me out.
No!
Our Chitanda has been
corrupted by Hotaro!
How could we have
let this happen?
There are evil spirits
roaming the halls of Kami high!
Ghosts hell-bent
on conserving energy!
Please, Chi, snap out of it!
[HOTARO] That's right,
laugh it up, you jerks.
[ERU]
I'm kidding.
--[SATOSHI] Huh?
--[MAYAKA] Huh?
I was just playing!
[HOTARO]
It was a joke?
And here I thought
I'd found my twin flame.
Sorry to scare you.
I just thought it'd be funny.
But it isn't like
I don't get angry.
Everyone does, even me!
Yeah, for example,
I get mad when...
I get really angry when I
see people wasting food.
In my house, a grain of rice
equals a drop of sweat.
[HOTARO] She's totally a
true farmer's daughter.
Hey, I almost forgot.
Speaking of flying
off the handle,
wasn't that you I heard
yelling at Mr. Omichi
during fifth period today?
[ERU gasps]
Yeah, you're right.
I can't believe
I forgot about that!
I want to hear your thoughts!
Tell me what you make of my
angry outburst today, Oreki!
[HOTARO]
Aw, crap.
[ERU ANGELS chattering]
Well... I gotta get going.
[ERU]
Wait!
Before you go, I just want
to hear what you think
about what happened!
Did something crazy go down?
[ERU] Yeah, as a matter
of fact, it was crazy!
I still can't believe it.
In math... I got angry.
Whoa. Chi, are
you kidding again?
[ERU]
No, I'm serious.
But I can't really figure out
what specifically made me mad,
only that I had gotten mad.
Ordinarily, I would
have made the choice
not to have gotten mad,
but I made the mad choice,
and now being made mad
makes me really curious.
Which kind of makes
the being made mad okay,
if you think about it.
Have you gone mad?
I was made mad
and then made curious
about being made mad!
Never mind the semantics!
I have to know!
[GIRL ATHLETES] Go! Fight!
Go! Fight! Go! Fight!
[ERU] Today my class
had math fifth period.
Mr. Omichi was teaching,
and in a bad mood.
Oreki and Fukube,
you guys have him, too,
so you know pretty well
what he can be like
when he gets himself riled up.
I guess I should
explain what happened
from the very beginning.
Let's see.
Mr. Omichi opened the
door to the classroom
right as the tardy
bell started to ring.
Before he came in, he
stopped outside the doorway
and looked up
at the class plate.
I guess so he would know
what class he was teaching.
But that's not unusual.
He does it every time.
Once he got in,
the first thing he did
was write a quadratic
equation up on the board.
It was simple enough, but he
did something new this time.
He included bounds for X,
which wasn't something
we knew how to do.
Then Omichi called on Kawasaki.
He told him to stand up
in front of the class
and solve the equation
for the range of Y.
Kawasaki froze.
He was confused,
which is only natural,
considering we hadn't
learned about ranges yet.
We were all nervous
at this point.
Kawasaki said that he didn't
know how to solve for Y,
which is what started it.
That's when Mr. Omichi
flipped out
and started screaming at us
for being bad students.
He calmed down after
a bit and called on Tamura,
who is really good at math.
Unfortunately, Tamura didn't
know what to do, either.
When the best guy at math
in the class didn't know,
I got the idea
that maybe Mr. Omichi
had been mistaken
about the lesson plan.
The other students must
have figured it out, too,
and things got a little chaotic.
Well, that really
set Mr. Omichi off,
so he started being
even harsher with us.
He even started beating the
chalkboard like a maniac,
which had never happened before.
Someone in class may have been
able to solve the problem,
but at that point,
no one wanted to speak up.
Everyone just stared
at their desks.
Then Mr. Omichi made
Tamura stand up again,
and started berating him,
trying to make an example
out of him, I guess.
That's when I just
couldn't take it anymore
and had to stand up.
I told Omichi he must be
mistaken and to double-check
our class's progress
in the lesson plan.
So now I see that's the
exact point when I got angry.
[MAYAKA]
Well, what happened next?
Let me see.
Then he just turned the
page in his textbook.
He saw something there
and said, "Oh, that's right."
Then he apologized.
After that, he told
Tamura to sit down
and continued teaching like
nothing had even happened.
So that's Mr. Omichi's
teaching style, huh?
Oh, for sure.
You would be traumatized
if I went into detail
about the kind of grief that
man gave me after midterms.
[HOTARO] We had teachers
like him back in elementary
and middle school,
though, right?
Ones with really bad tempers?
Besides, your crappy grades
are your own fault, not his.
You better study for the final.
[SATOSHI whines]
So anyway, that's the story.
What do you think?
Is anything about that
out of the ordinary?
Ah!
What I'm curious about
is how Mr. Omichi
made that kind of mistake
in the first place.
It seems so out of
character for him.
He's usually kind of a
perfectionist, so it's odd.
Yeah, you're right.
And I think the reason Omichi
is so strict with the students
is that he's equally
hard on himself.
So then how could he have
made such a simple mistake?
That's the part
I don't understand.
Yeah, weird.
I don't understand it either.
Hey, Oreki!
Beats me.
Look, if you really
wanna know that badly,
why don't you go
right to the source
and pick Omichi's
brain instead of mine?
Because that would take
all the fun out of it.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I guess you'll
never know the answer.
You might as well give it up.
I'm too curious for that!
Oreki, why don't you want to
think about this with me?
[HOTARO]
Why me?
Come on, silly, don't
you think it would be fun
for us to try to
figure this out together?
[SATOSHI]
Oh!
[HOTARO] I don't like
her talking to me like
I'm a little kid.
Look, Chi.
You might want to avoid
getting your hopes up
about this guy.
He was a sloth in
one of his past lives.
What? Mayaka, you can
do past life regression?
[HOTARO]
Nice distraction, Mayaka!
Interesting, but right now
I want to know about Omichi.
[HOTARO]
Damn! She won't be swayed.
I just... I have to know!
[ERU] Mr. Omichi always
makes a point to write a note
in his textbook at the
end of every class.
Why do you think he
takes the time to do that?
[HOTARO] So he can
remember how far he got
in each lesson and pick up
there for the next class.
[ERU]
That's what I thought.
He also does that weird
thing where he looks
at the class plate before
he comes in to the room.
It seems like a
fool-proof system,
so how is there room for
any mistakes on his part?
[HOTARO] He probably writes
the name of the class
and the date on the
page where they stopped.
Like, on page fifteen, "Class A,
July first," or something.
Otherwise, it would be really
easy for him to lose track.
Do you think maybe
he could have forgotten
what the date was?
If that were the case,
he would have gone
back a previous day,
not skipped ahead.
Use your brain a little, dummy.
Well, she's not wrong.
Something's bugging
me about this.
Wanna hear?
Of course, go ahead.
I can understand
you getting mad
about something like that.
But I can't imagine you
feeling so strongly about it
that you'd take the risk
to talk back to a teacher.
Why do you think you did?
I was angry,
but I didn't just speak up
because he was being mean to us.
That's not unusual
for Mr. Omichi.
[MAYAKA] Then, was it that the
people who knew the answer
didn't come forward?
No way.
Who would have wanted
to solve it in that situation,
even if they did
know the answer?
[MAYAKA] Could you have
been mad that no one else
had the courage to correct him?
Uh, no.
Do you think you just
felt sorry for him? Tamura?
I mean, I did feel
pretty bad for the guy.
But I can't imagine why
that would make me
mad enough to talk back.
It's kind of a regular
occurrence that a student
who doesn't know the
answer to a problem
we've already covered
in class would get berated
by the teacher, isn't it?
But as far as what made me
stand up to Mr. Omichi...
It's really hard to understand
ourselves sometimes.
You're right.
[HOTARO]
What pushes Chitanda's buttons?
What makes her tick?
I still don't feel like
I know her well enough
to be able to say
one way or the other.
So what's your take?
What do you think?
[HOTARO] The clue about
Omichi writing the note
in his book on
the class's progress
is the one that might
lead to an answer here.
But even doing that,
he still made a mistake.
Since it's math,
which is cumulative,
they're going in order,
so there had to be notes
written on the previous
pages in the chapter, too.
[HOTARO] You're absolutely
100% positive that your class
hadn't learned about ranges?
I'm sure. Positive.
Well, suppose you had
already learned about them,
then what?
I don't see what
you're getting at.
Omichi teaches the same
concepts every school term.
Class 1-A had the same lesson
last year, didn't they?
If you're saying he saw
the previous year's mark
and got confused, that
isn't a possible answer.
How can you be sure?
[SATOSHI] The teachers' editions
are replaced every year.
The publishers go through
and make slight corrections,
put in new problems, et cetera.
In order to make sure
they're all on the same page--
No pun intended--
they just reissue them.
They're currently
on the fourth edition.
I can't believe
you know that.
If it weren't for us,
all of your knowledge
would be useless.
Databases are never useless.
[HOTARO] Maybe Omichi
just wrote the wrong thing
in his book.
It could be the case, but...
I doubt that answer would
satisfy Chitanda's curiosity.
[SATOSHI] I gotta admit, I don't
understand ranges, either.
It's all I can do to put X
and Y in the same plane,
and even that's a chore,
which is kind of pathetic.
I'm gonna be in
for a world of pain
if Omichi sets his sights on me.
[HOTARO]
Wait a second.
Do you mean Class 1-D
has already covered
the ranges unit?
Oh, yeah. Mm-hmm.
[HOTARO] So Satoshi's class
would have been able
to solve the problem,
but Chitanda's couldn't.
Mine wouldn't have, either.
[HOTARO]
Then that's the answer.
Oh, man, I recognize that look.
You figured it out, huh?
[HOTARO]
I might have.
Chitanda.
Yes?
You're absolutely
certain there was a note
in the textbook farther
ahead than the point
your class had reached,
is that right?
Yes. No doubt about it.
[HOTARO] And it had to be
one he's written this year;
it was just not on the
page where Class 1-A
had actually stopped?
Right.
So what if we were
to assume that the note
was on the correct page,
just for the wrong class?
What if the note was a progress
marker for Satoshi's, not yours?
My class? Hmm...
[SATOSHI] Omichi teaches math
to four classes, A, B, C, and D.
Even if the note
wasn't for A or B,
that doesn't mean it
has to be for Class D.
And even if it
was for that class,
why would it matter?
Well, if that were the case,
it makes sense that he would
mistake the mark for Class A's.
There's not much chance he'd
confuse a C for a D, is there?
Huh? Now you're
talking nonsense again.
No one would mistake
an A for a D, either.
[HOTARO]
But Omichi is a mathematician.
[MAYAKA]
Yeah, so what?
That's why it's likely.
It's really easy to
mistake those two letters
when you do math.
How?
[HOTARO] Let's say on
page 10 Omichi wrote,
"July first, Class A,"
then on page 15
he would have written,
"July first, Class D."
Does that make sense?
[MAYAKA] Okay, so what
exactly are you getting at?
Why would anyone confuse
one for the other?
[HOTARO]
Just assume he did for a sec.
If so, then what went down today
is pretty likely, right?
[MAYAKA]
Huh?
[ERU] Wait... I don't get
how that would ever happen.
'Cause when you
write equations,
A and D would look like this.
I get it! He thought a
lowercase D was an A!
You solved it!
[groans]
I guess you're right.
One time, on an English
test, I lost points
because the teacher
couldn't tell some of my
lowercase letters apart.
Same here. It's difficult.
On my test, the teacher couldn't
distinguish the Ns from the Hs.
That's what happened.
It seems so obvious now.
[HOTARO]
Man. I'm glad that's settled.
Huh?
D and A.
I can't blame him
for mixing those up.
I feel bad now.
I guess I was a bit out
of line for getting so mad
and yelling, huh?
I'm surprised I didn't
get in trouble for it.
What?! How can you say that?
He was a total "D" and screamed
at the class for no good reason!
You have to stand up
for what's right!
Hey, calm down.
Just look at how
late it's gotten.
Don't you think it's
time we headed home?
[MAYAKA] But wait...
I wasn't finished.
[SATOSHI] I know,
but why does it matter?
The mystery's been solved.
[MAYAKA]
Hey! I'm not done with you!
[HOTARO] Chitanda, who's
usually slow to anger,
got mad today and
had to know why.
She said herself that wrath
isn't necessarily a bad thing.
But I wonder...
For some reason, she still
seems to avoid getting riled up.
Could her quest to
pinpoint the cause
of her anger have been
motivated by some desire
to let Omichi off the hook?
Did she just want
to find some proof
that she was wrong to get
mad in the first place?
Is that the kind of person Eru
Chitanda really is, at her core?
Nah.
Who am I kidding.
I don't truly know her at all.
Even if I knew her well
enough to make predictions
about her behavior,
if I ever presumed to be able
to read her mind, well...
I know what that'd be.
A cardinal sin. Pride.
One of the seven deadly ones.
Avoid those at
all costs, they say.
I mean, come on.
How many times has
Chitanda surprised me,
in this afternoon alone?
[ERU]
Hey, Oreki.
Aren't you coming with us?
Oh. Of course. I'm sorry.
[ERU]
Hey, listen.
Thank you for your
help with everything.
I mean it feels like
you're always solving
these mysteries
for me, doesn't it?
Yeah, and it's becoming
a real hassle.
[ERU chuckles]
What are you guys still
waiting around for?
Yeah, you wanna
live at the school?
No. We're right behind you.
Well, should we be going, then?
Sure.
[HOTARO] I guess tomorrow
I'll pick up where I left off.
[ERU]
C'mon, Oreki!
That may be true
for you, Mayaka.
Think about it from
her perspective.
[HOTARO] And so, another
afternoon of my high school life
is spent squandering my energy.
I've got my hands full
with one deadly sin, sloth.
That's plenty for now.
[ERU] Next time:
"Upon Seeing The True Nature."