[STUDENTS shouting]
[HOTARO] They say high school
is all sunshine and roses.
Sunshine, roses,
rainbows, and unicorns.
I've heard so much about
the bliss and excitement
of being a high school student
that I've written it off
as a worn out cliché.
Who's to say that all teenagers
even want high school
to be like some
fairy tale fever dream?
It seems ridiculous to me.
There's all the studying,
and the sports hysteria,
and the saccharin-sweet
romantic affairs.
Those are the worst.
A lot of teenagers
have no interest
in that kind of
nonsense, right?
[HOTARO]
Well...
I guess when you
rule out all that crap,
there's not much
left over, is there?
Wow, Hotaro,
I never knew you were such
a full-fledged pessimist.
[HOTARO]
Wait, a pessimist?
Why have you got a problem with
studying, sports, romance?
Things the normal kids enjoy.
You make it sound so dismal.
[HOTARO]
That's not what I said.
You misunderstood me.
I'm telling you what I hear.
Maybe you're just lazy.
What do you think of that?
Anytime you think
something's a hassle
or seems like it might be
frivolous, you refuse to do it!
Which explains... your motto!
"If I don't have to,
I'm not going to.
And if I have to, I'll do it
as quickly as possible."
That's the one.
But just so you know,
by not joining any of the
offerings at the veritable
Mecca of clubs which
we call Kamiyama High,
you've made a little black
cloud appear above your head.
You might think you're slick,
but you're only
punishing yourself.
You've crossed over
into downright masochism.
You sure like
to run your mouth.
You're just now noticing?
We've been friends
since middle school.
Whatever. Go without me.
What do you mean,
"without you"?
What the--?!
Is that what I think it is?
A club application?
Hotaro! You're joining one?
Classic Lit club? Really?
--[HOTARO] Oh, you know it?
--[SATOSHI] Of course I do!
Since when are you
into classic lit?
[SATOSHI]
What's that?
What does a letter from your
sister have to do with it?
[HOTARO]
She sent it to me from India.
Some place in the
north called Varanasi.
Oh, yeah?
I see what's going on.
Your sister's blackmailing you.
[HOTARO] They're threatening
to shut it down
for lack of members.
She wants me to join and
help keep the club alive.
But I thought your sister
was more into martial arts.
[HOTARO] Aikido, actually,
which is worse.
If she wants to hurt you,
she knows just how to do it.
[SATOSHI laughs]
Then you should
do what she says!
[HOTARO] Well, it's not like
I have anything better to do,
and believe me, I've tried
to think of an excuse.
[SATOSHI] So the club
doesn't have any members?
[HOTARO]
Nope.
Well, then look
on the bright side:
You'll have the clubroom
all to yourself!
[SATOSHI] It'll be nice to have
your own private space
on school grounds, at least.
Sounds like a dream!
"My own private space?"
[TEAM CAPTAIN]
Come on, ladies!
[HOTARO] I salute people who
have that kind of energy.
[HOTARO]
Knock, knock.
[HOTARO] People usually
misunderstand me on this.
It's not like I think
my way of doing things
is better than theirs,
by any means.
And I don't see
myself as superior
to those who choose
to get involved.
I'm just true to
my motto, that's all.
If I don't have to,
I'm not going to.
And if I have to, I'll do
it as quickly as possible.
There, see?
Ew!
[HOTARO] Fourth floor
of the auxiliary building.
That's as remote as it gets.
Hello, there.
I didn't know you were in
the Classic Literature club.
Oreki, right?
Who're you?
Oh, you don't know?
My name's Eru. Eru Chitanda.
Sorry. I have
no idea who you are.
Hotaro Oreki
from class 1-B?
That is your name, isn't it?
Yeah.
I'm in class 1-A,
so we have met.
I'm sorry, but...
That's not ringing
any bells, so...
[HOTARO] 1-A?
Maybe we share an elective.
Wait a sec,
you wouldn't happen to be
in my music class, would you?
Yep!
[HOTARO] We've only had that
class once so far this term.
Her memory is incredible.
[HOTARO]
So, uh, Chitanda...
What are you doing in here?
Are you lost or something?
Nope!
You see, I joined
the Classic Lit club.
This is where it says
we're supposed to meet!
[ERU]
I joined the Classic Lit club.
Are you for real?
Why would you do that?
I have my reasons, but
they're kind of personal.
Why did you join?
Oh, uh...
No reason really, I'm
just glad we have members.
[HOTARO]
Are you happy now, Sis?
Classic Lit club lives
to see another day.
[HOTARO]
Well, see ya later.
[ERU]
Wait, you're leaving already?
[HOTARO]
Sure am. Have fun in here.
And be sure to lock up
when you leave.
[ERU]
What?
I can't lock up
if I don't have a key.
What's that?
I was saying that
I don't have a key.
Oh, yeah.
Here.
Wait a sec...
Why do you have the key
to this room, Oreki?
[HOTARO]
What do you mean by that?
How in the hell was
I supposed to get into
a locked classroom without one?
Pardon my French. I'm confused.
I don't understand how you
got in before I showed up.
The door was open
when I got here.
[HOTARO] Well, then you must
have just locked it behind you.
[BOTH gasp]
Are you saying what I think?
I was locked in here?
Yeah, you were.
So someone came along
and trapped me
alone in this room
until you showed up?
Look, I'm sure you
just did it yourself.
Are you certain that you didn't?
Yes, I'm absolutely certain!
But I'm the only one with a key.
I mean what else could have
possibly happened here?
Maybe we should ask the guy
who's hiding in the hallway.
Huh?
[HOTARO]
Satoshi...
[SATOSHI]
Hey! Sorry about that.
I totally didn't mean to
eavesdrop on you guys.
You "totally" did.
[SATOSHI]
Okay, guilty as charged.
But I gotta admit, when I
see my good buddy, Hotaro,
known for his stoicism,
in an empty classroom
with a young lady,
and dusk fast approaching,
I get more than
a little curious.
I had no intention
of barging in--
[ERU]
Hey!
We weren't--
No! I wasn't--!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Of course. Just joking.
Oh, thank goodness.
Sorry 'bout that.
This guy has no manners at all.
Nothing beats a good joke!
"Don't ever take
life too seriously."
I live by that motto.
Right.
Oreki, who is this boy?
[HOTARO] This is Satoshi Fukube,
would-be comedian.
I see.
Hey, good one!
I'm honored that you
think so, my good friend.
Nice to meet you.
And you are...?
I'm Eru Chitanda.
Did you say Chitanda?
As in the very famous Chitandas?
What's the matter with you?
[SATOSHI] Wait, are you telling
me you've never heard
of the Chitanda family?
Kamiyama has more than
a few prestigious dynasties.
But none of them are as notable
as the four
Higher Power Families.
[SATOSHI] There's the
shrine-owning Jumonji family,
the Sasusuberi
Bookstore Tycoons,
the wealthy Chitanda farmers,
and the Maninbashi landowners.
Written this way,
the kanji for each name
increases by the power
of ten, hence the name
"Higher Power Families."
Is that true?
I wouldn't say we're
a prestigious family.
And I've never heard us
referred to by that name before.
You made up the name.
It sounds cool,
and I thought I could be
the one to coin the phrase.
They really increase
by powers of ten, huh?
Don't act so impressed.
He'll get a big ego.
They also say the
oldest Chitanda girl
is known for her beauty
and incredible grades.
And that she's the most refined
girl in all of Kamiyama.
In middle school,
she got a perfect score
on the prefectural exams, and
the school board went crazy!
No way. Is he right?
It's just a fluke.
I have a knack for acing
standardized tests.
[SATOSHI]
Well, I beg your pardon.
Anyway, I happened to
hear you guys talking.
Wow, what a mystery, am I right?
[HOTARO]
I'm not following.
[SATOSHI] How in the heck did
Chitanda get locked inside
this room earlier?
Oh, I forgot!
When I showed up,
the door to this room
was most definitely unlocked.
But when Oreki got here,
it was bolted,
and he had to use his key
to get inside, so what happened?
Well, that's easy.
You must have locked it when
you came in and forgotten.
Try again!
Kami High School's doors can
only be locked using a key,
from the inside or the outside.
So that means it's not
even possible for Chitanda
to have locked herself in!
That's crazy!
Man, you've always been
such a know-it-all.
I prefer the term
"database," sir.
Well, I'm sure there's
a reasonable explanation
for this whole lock thing.
See you guys later.
No, please don't go just yet!
Why not?
I have to know.
How did I come to be locked
in this room like that?
And if the door was
supposed to be locked,
why was it open when I got here?
Did someone leave
it open on purpose?
And if they did, why?
If not, how did they lock it
again without me noticing?
I beg you, Oreki,
think about it carefully.
I need your help.
Please. I have to know!
Yeah. Okay. I'll help.
It is interesting, after all.
Thank you so very much!
So do you have any ideas,
just off the top of your head?
Whoa, Chitanda.
Give him some time.
While I'm full of
useless information
and can't make any deductions,
Hotaro is the opposite.
Once he's had
some time to think,
his conclusions
are fairly accurate.
That's enough.
Let's see.
So how long were
you here before me?
[ERU] It couldn't have more
than about three minutes.
Did you notice
anything unusual?
Well, actually...
I've been hearing this
weird rattling below us
this whole time.
[SATOSHI]
What? I don't hear anything.
[ERU]
It's really faint. Listen.
[SATOSHI]
You must have really sharp ears.
[SATOSHI] So... Have you
figured anything out yet?
[HOTARO]
Maybe.
I bet the culprit is on the
floor below us right now.
[JANITOR]
Last one. Good.
[SATOSHI]
A-ha.
Chitanda must have
gone into the room
while the maintenance
guy was working,
and accidentally gotten locked
inside without knowing it.
I have the regular key
to the science room
in my pocket.
I know the janitor has a master,
and they don't give
those out to students.
That's how you knew
he was working.
But still... You guessed
that just from a noise!
Yeah, I did.
Anyway, I still don't understand
why you didn't notice
the sound of the door
locking when you were inside
the science room, if you
could hear the janitor
through the floor.
Ah. A simple explanation.
I was distracted
by that old building.
[SATOSHI]
It's ancient!
[ERU]
Yep.
Is it really?
Yeah. Look at it!
[ERU] By the way, I think we
should talk about the club.
[HOTARO]
Oh, that's right.
[ERU]
Yeah.
From the look of things,
I'd say it's only going
to be the three of us.
"Three of us?"
[ERU] Fukube, what do
you think? Wanna join?
Why not? I sure had
a lot of fun today.
I'll have to juggle
Executive Committee
and handicrafts, but uh...
Yep! I'm in!
Hotaro is in, too.
He's already filled
out the application.
Have you really?
Huh? Yeah, I filled it out.
[ERU]
Great.
Huh?
Right! I'll turn this in!
I'm really looking forward
to seeing you again.
Yeah, same here!
And Hotaro is, too.
[ERU] I guess we're gonna have
to choose a club president!
Who should we pick?
[SATOSHI]
Huh, good question.
I don't think Hotaro would
be the best candidate.
[HOTARO]
Well, there you have it, Sis.
Your precious Classic
Literature Club
lives to see another term.
As a result, my dreams of
conserving energy are dead.
No! I'm not gonna lay them
to rest without a fight.
I refuse to give up my
peace of mind that easily.
I will devote all my efforts
to doing as little as possible.
There's just one problem.
...and the tranquil
temperament of a great leader!
[HOTARO]
That little lady.
[SATOSHI] It happened
yesterday after school.
A first year girl climbed
to the fourth floor
of the auxiliary building.
When she arrived,
she heard the somber strains
of "Moonlight Sonata"
coming from the music room.
The setting sun bathed the
hallway in a crimson glow.
The warm tones--
[HOTARO]
Objection. It rained all day.
You couldn't see the sunset.
[SATOSHI]
Fine.
It was a dark and
gloomy afternoon,
and dusk was drawing near.
A feeling of unease
clung to the girl,
and the rain on her
skin made her shiver.
[HOTARO]
You're embellishing.
[SATOSHI]
Lured by the mysterious tones,
she entered the room.
Immediately, the music stopped.
The lid of the piano was up,
but no one was
seated at the keys.
The drawn curtains
and gloomy weather
made the room darker than usual.
That's when she saw her!
A female student with
long, messy hair
hanging over her face, was
slumped over across the room!
Her eyes were so bloodshot
they almost glowed.
As the apparition stared
menacingly at our heroine...
[GIRL screams]
[SATOSHI] It was the ghost of a
piano club member of the past,
who had met a tragic end
in that very room,
minutes before a
national competition!
[HOTARO]
Oh, really?
Huh? Well...
I don't know about that part for
sure, but it's not impossible.
[HOTARO]
Yeah, that's what I thought.
[SATOSHI] I've gotta say,
this is a surprise.
I don't think you've ever
forgotten your homework
in all the years I've known you.
I didn't forget to do it.
I just left it at home this
morning, that's all.
So now I have to
stay after class
and write the same
stupid essay again,
while you talk my ear off.
Yeah, lucky you.
Anyway, I heard there really
was a crazy-haired ghost
in the music room.
That's all anyone in class A
could talk about
during lunch today.
The real question is how
quickly the story will spread
through the rest of the school.
And if it will change at all.
It's one of the seven wonders
of Kamiyama High School.
Number two! You know?
I'm interested to see
how many days it takes
the news to spread
to D, my class.
Hold on a second.
Exactly when, where, and from
whom did you hear this story?
[SATOSHI] Earlier today, in the
club room, from Chitanda.
If the music room
ghost is the second
of the seven wonders,
what's the first?
I'm sure you're
dying to tell me.
Hey!
I suspected I might
find you two in here.
I wrote it up for you.
Here ya go.
Thanks, I appreciate that.
I'm sorry.
As a member of the
Executive Committee,
I'm forced to delegate some of
my responsibilities to others.
No worries!
After all, I am the
club president now.
[ERU]
Hi, Oreki!
[HOTARO] You came at
the perfect time!
Satoshi just finished telling me
quite an interesting story.
Yeah! I'm glad
you brought that up!
I heard it at lunch!
[HOTARO] It's about the
mysterious Secret Club
Recruitment Notes.
Have you heard it?
A secret club?
[HOTARO] Yes, why don't you
tell her the story, Satoshi?
Huh?
Well, what do you say?
Wanna hear it?
Honestly, it's
pretty fascinating.
Yes.
Ahem.
I heard it today at the
Executive Committee meeting.
Well, you already know this
school has a million clubs.
So of course there are
recruitment posters
plastered all over the place.
There are so many
that the bulletin boards
get buried underneath them.
When the Executive Committee
finds unauthorized posts,
we take them down.
No exceptions.
However...
For the past few years, a
strange recruitment note
has been turning up,
and no one claims to know
a thing about it.
Last year, it showed up
as a scrap of notebook paper
with just a meeting place
and time scribbled on it.
This club has been gathering,
conducting secret business,
and recruiting new members,
all without the Executive
Committee's knowledge.
No one knows for sure who
they are or what they do,
but we do have one
piece of information:
Their name.
[ERU]
Yeah, what is it?
Joro Spider Society.
Joro Spider?
So you know Tanabe,
the chair of the
Executive Committee?
Well, he tried to bust
them up last year
by going to the
alleged meeting place
at the exact time the note said.
That plan didn't
go over so well.
He didn't find anything
and decided it was a hoax
to make the
committee look stupid.
However...
[ERU]
What happened?
[SATOSHI] On graduation day,
one of the departing students
pulled him aside and said...
"I was the president
of the Joro Spider Society.
Please give my warm
regards to the one
who succeeds me.
Which will be hard,
because we will ensure that
you never unveil his identity."
[SATOSHI] They're likely
recruiting new members
for this year, too.
But we haven't been able to
find their secret base yet.
The cryptic recruitment note
of Joro Spider Society!
That's it. I must know!
[HOTARO]
Yes!
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Which is why I said you
came at the perfect time.
And what do you mean by that?
You're just in time
for the next step:
To find the note.
Right!
[SATOSHI] There's a total
of 30 bulletin boards
throughout the school.
[ERU]
That many?
Are we going to
search all of them?
[HOTARO]
No, we're not.
It's faster to just
search the boards
where they're most
likely to hide the note.
[ERU]
That makes sense.
[HOTARO] Where would you put
a secret recruitment note?
[ERU]
Well, if it were up to me...
I think I'd pin it to one
of the corner bulletin boards,
where it would attract as
little attention as possible.
[HOTARO] That's where
you're wrong, though.
[ERU]
Wait, why is that?
[HOTARO] Remember that
the purpose of this note
is to recruit new members,
so they'd probably put it
on the board at the
first floor entrance.
[ERU]
What?
But everyone in school
would see it, wouldn't they?
[SATOSHI]
Hold on, Chitanda.
I'm sure Hotaro has a
brilliant idea up his sleeve.
Wow!
It's pretty impressive that our
school has all these clubs!
Kinda hard to believe.
[ERU]
It is remarkable.
A calligraphy club, a
basketball club, a track club.
The list just keeps going.
There's barely any open
space left on the board.
Hey, Oreki.
Are you doing okay?
Yeah.
I'm just a little overwhelmed
by all this activity, I guess.
[SATOSHI laughs]
This world must be unfathomable
to our energy-conserving
friend here.
Anyway, since this is the first
bulletin board the students see,
it's become a battleground.
Wait, what does that mean?
Oh, right, I get it!
With so many clubs
competing to get noticed,
an unauthorized post
could slip under the radar.
[HOTARO]
That's part of it.
"Part of it"?
Wait, what could some
other reasons be?
You'll see.
Let's just start
looking around, okay?
Right!
[ERU] There's the Environmental
Club, Debate Club,
even a Hundred Poets
Card Game Club.
The Fortune-telling Club!
I have a good friend who just
joined that one this year.
Oh, yeah?
Koto Club. Ping Pong Club.
The Art Club.
It doesn't seem like
there's anything here
for the Joro Spider Society.
I don't know.
You might not be able
to tell what their
secret recruitment note
is just by looking at it.
[ERU]
What? What do you mean by that?
[SATOSHI] Well, they might
have come up with a code
to keep the Executive Committee
from finding them out.
A code. I see.
Uh-huh.
But if it's here,
we're gonna break it.
[HOTARO]
Found something.
[ERU]
Huh?
There it is, all right.
I would imagine they'd
pick a more crowded place
on the board to hide it.
Definitely the work of amateurs.
They're inexperienced first
years trying to be rebels.
If this secret club knew
at all what they were doing,
our job would have
been much harder.
That's a good point.
It's still weird, though.
Their lack of any real skill
is painfully obvious,
now that you mention it.
But I'm not actually
surprised in the least.
No stamp of approval
from the Committee?
Well...
I'd better report this.
[HOTARO]
All right.
I'm gonna stop by the faculty
room to turn in my essay,
then start to head home.
Yeah, okay.
I guess I'll walk
along with you, then.
It is getting late.
Until the next time
we meet, then, gentlemen.
"Inexperienced first years
trying to be rebels."
I'll never forget that.
Well, your "fight mystery
with mystery" plan
was a real success.
I applaud you.
Yeah, thanks for all your help.
For some reason I had a feeling
she was coming to find us.
[SATOSHI]
Ah!
So that's why you wrote the
note and got the pin ready.
Well, looks like you have
a knack for deception.
I'm curious, though.
Why did you go to
so much trouble to set up
that elaborate ruse
just to distract her
from the music room mystery?
Don't tell me that
silly ghost story
actually freaked you
out or something.
[HOTARO] The music room
was too far away.
Are you kidding?
No, I'm not.
I wanted to find a way to get
us close to the main entrance,
wrap up the mystery so
I could turn in my essay,
and get the heck
out of there fast.
I wish I could
say I'm surprised.
That's typical Hotaro.
Please. I have to know!
If I have to do something,
I'll do it as quickly
as possible. Right?
[SATOSHI]
No way.
You won't get away with that.
If you're gonna
proclaim your motto,
do it with your head held
high and don't paraphrase!
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you were just
making a sorry excuse.
[SATOSHI] Distracting from one
mystery with another mystery?
I approve. Nice curveball.
But you know something, Hotaro?
What you did today
wasn't really your style.
When Chitanda showed up,
why didn't you
just blow her off,
like the lazy bones
we know and love?
That was your fatal
mistake this afternoon.
You'd have been home already.
Sometimes, you don't
know how to best live
by your own motto.
Maybe you're right.
"Inexperienced first years
trying to be rebels."
That's exactly what you were
today, as a matter of fact.
Chitanda is throwing you
off your game, my friend.
I didn't expect that of you.
I wondered why you took
such a meandering detour.
I understand you were trying
to trick Chitanda and all,
but there are
more efficient ways.
Anyway--
I wasn't actually
trying to trick her.
No, of course you weren't.
You were just putting the
situation on hold for later.
On hold?
Oh, yeah. That's right!
[SATOSHI chuckles]
[SATOSHI]
Speaking of the other situation,
what do you make of
the music room thing?
[HOTARO]
Right.
Well, the alleged ghost
had messed-up hair
and bloodshot eyes,
which sounds like someone
who just woke up from a nap.
Oh. You're right.
[HOTARO] Some Piano Club
member got sleepy
and decided to have a rest.
She was nervous that
she'd sleep past six o'clock,
when they lock up,
so she set the alarm
on the cd player and
put in "Moonlight Sonata."
It's as simple as that.
[SATOSHI]
That makes sense.
I'm sure if we'd checked it out,
we'd have known what
happened right away.
The music room was too far away.
Yeah, I hear that.
Even so, you know what?
[HOTARO]
Hm?
[SATOSHI] I have a feeling
you wasted a lot of time
by avoiding the trip.
You'd have conserved more
energy by checking it out.
Be careful next time.
This might end up costing you
more than you think.
[HOTARO]
Hm?
This is me!
Don't worry! I don't judge!
And I'm not gonna
hold it over your head!
Bye!
[HOTARO]
On hold, huh? Right.
Next time:
"The Prestigious Classic
Lit Club's Activities."