[HOTARO] I bet if I picked up
a microphone and said,
"Today, the weather
will be pleasant,"
anyone from Japan who
heard me would just think,
"Oh, Oreki must be
testing that microphone."
Ten seconds left.
[HOTARO] But people from
other countries would think
I was giving a forecast.
They'd assume I
just wanted them to know
it would be clear.
[TEACHER 19A] Okay, time's up.
Pass your papers to the front.
[HOTARO] Both assumptions
could be considered reasonable.
Both parties have a fifty-fifty
shot at being right.
It all depends on luck.
What's the world coming to, man?
[HOTARO]
I've been wondering...
Your uncle Jun.
Did everything go all right
with his funeral?
It turned out very well.
Thank you.
Oh, good.
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just...
Oreki...
Could you do me a favor?
Do you think that you could
light some incense for my uncle?
You want me to?
Yes, please.
I am planning to make a
trip out to his gravesite
in the next few of days or so.
And, well...
I hoped you'd... come with me.
Yeah, sure.
I'll go.
Oh, great!
I'll be in touch with you
about the details soon.
[HOTARO]
Cool.
I just have to
tell you, Oreki,
you have a gift when
it comes to mysteries,
and I'm grateful that you
solved the one about my uncle.
I think you're amazing.
You know, I appreciate
the sentiment,
but I've always
just gotten lucky.
I wish you wouldn't treat me
like I'm a big deal or whatever.
You sure are humble.
That's impressive.
[HOTARO]
Aw, man...
She totally missed the point.
[HOTARO] Chitanda, I heard
something once upon a time
that struck me as profound.
What is that?
"You can put poultice and
plausible reason on anything."
[giggling]
Oreki, the saying goes,
"You can put plaster and
plausible reason on anything."
[HOTARO]
Uh... That's what it says?
I just mean you
can find reasons
to support anything you want.
If you say so.
Then the reason you've
solved all these cases
is only pure, dumb luck,
and it has nothing to do
with your intelligence.
And your talent isn't
a factor either, okay?
However, you've been
able to capitalize
on the luck you've had,
and follow through
to the correct conclusions.
Now isn't that,
in and of itself,
a particular kind of talent?
Are you trying to say
I'm a master of reason?
[ERU]
Am I wrong?
Yeah, you are.
I couldn't tell you how
I made those deductions.
Honestly, that's
the real mystery here.
[ERU]
If I had to guess,
what I would say...
...is that you have never
really taken a good,
honest look at yourself.
[HOTARO]
She's not wrong there.
In that case, Chitanda,
I want you to come up
with a situation.
I'll prove to you
that I can invent
a good reason for it,
whatever it is.
This is a dream come true!
[HOTARO]
This is the perfect opportunity
to show her that she
can't actually rely on me.
All right, then.
What should I pick for you?
[PA announcement]
[SHIBAZAKI] Anyone who
was shopping at Kobundo
near the train station
on October 31st,
please report to Shibazaki in
the faculty room immediately.
[ERU]
What is that all about?
No clue.
Let's make that the situation!
Please deduce why that
announcement was made just now!
So what's the story behind it?
Okay, fine.
Challenge accepted.
Right. Here ya go.
[HOTARO] Your power of
recollection is as intimidating
as ever.
That's no compliment.
Let's see...
"Anyone who was
shopping at Kobundo
near the train station
on October 31st,
please report to Shibazaki in
the faculty room immediately."
First thing we should
do is a word check.
Do you know what
this "Kobundo" is?
Yes.
It's a little stationery store
across from the train station.
[ERU] It's very quaint, and it's
run by a sweet elderly couple.
I've only been
there once, though.
[HOTARO]
What kind of stationery?
[ERU]
Oh, the usual.
North Elementary is nearby,
so I think they might specialize
in the kinds of things
grade-schoolers would use.
[HOTARO] So it's not
the kind of place where
high-schoolers would go
out of their way to shop?
[ERU]
I suppose you could say that.
[HOTARO] Is Shibazaki
on the faculty here?
Oreki, Mr. Shibazaki
is the vice principal.
[giggles]
For all your deductive prowess,
you're not good with
remembering people's names, huh?
Leave me alone.
[HOTARO] "If I don't have to,
I'm not going to.
If I have to, I'll do it
as quickly as possible."
That was my unshakeable creed.
But the stakes of
this contest are high.
I'm going to have to turn up
the heat a little on this one.
First off...
[ERU]
Yes?
I've deduced why Shibazaki
would be calling
people in to see him.
Yes. I have a pretty good
idea of that myself.
[HOTARO]
Just to make things clearer,
let's refer to the student
who's been called out as "X."
[ERU] Now we're getting
into the swing of things.
Why don't you have a seat?
Okay.
[HOTARO clears throat]
At this point,
with the information we have,
there's no way to know
whether X is a single kid
or multiple people.
Could be anything.
A teaching moment.
He could be trying
to teach X a lesson
about something that happened.
In other words,
he could be calling X
to the faculty room
to chew them out.
What makes you so
certain about that?
Because when students are
called down to the faculty room,
it's very rarely
for something good.
That's what you call
inductive reasoning.
Oreki, are you
taking this seriously?
I haven't been this
serious about something
since I started at Kami High.
I'd go so far as to say
I haven't been this serious
my whole life.
Besides, if he was summoning X
to the faculty room
to offer praise,
he wouldn't put it
in such vague terms.
he would just say that's
what was going on.
And he would have called
the person out by name.
With an announcement like that,
anyone involved would be
too anxious to answer it.
[ERU] You're right,
that's a good point.
Furthermore, that sounded
like an urgent page.
You mean 'cause
he said, "immediately"?
[HOTARO]
No, most pages use that word.
It's not that.
This announcement deviated
from the standard pattern,
so we can deduce that
they made it hastily.
[ERU]
Standard pattern? How so?
[HOTARO] Let's say you wanted
to make an announcement
addressing me, asking me
to come to Class 1-A.
What would you say?
Well, let me see...
Something like this:
"Attention, students:
Would Hotaro Oreki of class 1-B
please report to Eru Chitanda
in the 1-A classroom."
Is that really all?
Try to think of
other announcements
you've heard this year.
If it were me, I'd say:
"Attention: would Eru
Chitanda of Class 1-A
please report to Hotaro Oreki
in Class 1-B at once.
I repeat.
Would Eru Chitanda of Class 1-A
please report to Hotaro Oreki
in the 1-B classroom at once."
[HOTARO] It's not like
a regular announcement.
Usually summons like that
are repeated somehow.
But for whatever reason,
he only made this
announcement once.
I think it's safe to
conclude he was in a rush.
It's not just any
run-of-the-mill rush, either.
It's not?
I know that because
of when we heard it.
He made the announcement
after school.
Hmm... I don't know.
That seems pretty
insignificant, if you ask me.
[HOTARO]
Oh, yeah?
Then I won't say
why I think that.
Oreki, come on!
It's just a bit odd.
Why make that announcement
after school?
Why not make it
earlier in the day?
Sure, Kamiyama may have
a ton of after-school
clubs and activities,
but there are still
plenty of students here
who leave right away.
That makes me think he
made the announcement
after school because
the event that caused
the announcement happened
after school, too.
And it was urgent enough
that he couldn't risk
waiting to summon X
until tomorrow.
So that means Shibazaki
followed his impulse
and took the gamble
that X hadn't gone home
from school yet.
I gotta say...
This whole thing feels
incredibly shady to me.
Yeah, me, too.
And the term "shady,"
how did it come to
mean what it does?
Dunno.
[whining]
[HOTARO]
Next deduction...
Whatever Shibazaki wants
to speak to X about,
that subject can't be
discussed out in the open.
Whether that's just
for now or forever,
we have no way of knowing.
[ERU] Do you figure
that because Shibazaki
didn't give a reason
for making the page?
[HOTARO]
That's a factor,
but there's an even
clearer reason I think so.
[ERU]
It's not clear to me.
Shibazaki is the
vice-principal, right?
The guidance counselor
is usually the one
who comes down on students.
[ERU]
That's right.
Morishita is always the
one to call students in.
Where is the guidance
counselor's office?
It's on the second floor
of the main building.
[HOTARO] But Shibazaki summoned
X to the faculty room,
and not the guidance
counselor's office.
To me, that means the
circumstances were serious.
And that all information
about this incident
was to be kept between
the administration only.
Or so it could be argued.
Listen... Oreki...
[HOTARO]
What is it?
Judging by what you've deduced
about this situation so far,
I can't escape the feeling
that X was involved
in doing something really bad.
Well, that's what
all the signs point to.
[ERU gasps]
So then...
[HOTARO]
Student X...
...committed some kind of crime.
[HOTARO] This is only a game
between Chitanda and me.
My explanation doesn't have
to match up with the truth.
I mean, the whole point
of this was to prove
that my assessments
are only right
when I have a good deal
of luck on my side.
So, then... What crime
could X have committed?
[HOTARO]
Before we get to that,
if we assume that my
deductions are accurate,
we have to note that the school
doesn't have a police officer,
so it's likely that
law enforcement
has been summoned
here to talk to X
about what went down.
If a crime was committed,
it must have happened
on October 31st.
And yet the announcement
came a few minutes ago,
and seemed really hurried.
It's conceivable that the
page followed immediately
after some request
from law enforcement.
[ERU] But that could have
been done relatively easily
over the phone.
[HOTARO]
That may be true,
but if worse came to worse,
and it was decided
that X was guilty,
the police might have
to take X into custody.
They could have come to
the school just in case
that became necessary.
Custody?
Do you mean if
X is found guilty
that they would
face criminal charges?
Well, it's possible.
Hey. It's a game, remember?
Oh. Right. I keep forgetting.
If X weren't the culprit,
Shibazaki would have waited
to make the announcement,
and he wouldn't have
sounded so rushed.
[ERU]
That makes sense.
[HOTARO] Now as far
as what crime we may
be dealing with here,
do you have any ideas?
It must have to do
with the store somehow.
Well, let's see... Uh...
Shoplifting is
the obvious choice.
Beyond that,
it's possible that someone
had committed crimes
at other locations,
but police received a testimony
that someone of that
suspect's description
had been seen
shopping at Kobundo,
but if that's the case,
the crime could have been
any number of heinous acts.
It could have been anything!
[HOTARO] That's a detailed
answer for having been
put on the spot.
[HOTARO] Considering
the announcement,
I doubt anyone gave
a physical description.
[ERU]
Why's that?
[HOTARO] If the police had
a description of someone
who had committed a crime,
they would probably
share it with Shibazaki.
He would have been able
to think of at least one name,
and wouldn't just have said,
"anyone who was
shopping at Kobundo"
in the announcement.
[ERU]
That's a good point.
[HOTARO] The incident
occurred at Kobundo,
and all we know
for sure was that X
was shopping there
on October 31st.
[HOTARO] Was the purpose of
the announcement to make X
turn themselves in?
If that's the case, it's
kind of a weird way to do it.
[HOTARO]
I speculate...
...that law enforcement doesn't
know very much about X,
but they assume that
the announcement
will lead X to
confess their crimes.
[ERU]
Why would that be?
[HOTARO]
If I had done something wrong,
and that page came
over the PA system...
[PA announcement]
[SHIBAZAKI] Anyone who
was shopping at Kobundo
near the train station
on October 31st,
please report to Shibazaki in
the faculty room immediately.
[TEACHER 19A]
Ten more seconds.
[HOTARO]
Good.
The police still don't know
I'm the one who did it.
If all goes according to plan,
I could get away with it
and go on to become
a criminal mastermind!
[laughing]
[HOTARO] Why would a guilty
party ever come forward
just because they heard
an announcement like that?
If they had some sense of
remorse about the crime?
No, if that were the case,
they'd have turned
themselves in already,
and wouldn't be at large.
What are you thinking?
Let's forget about
the nature of the crime
for a moment, and
try another tactic.
Now suppose X felt guilty
about what they had done.
Maybe they decided to apologize
to the owners of Kobundo.
In writing.
Wait, in writing?
Chitanda.
Do you know the date
off the top of your head?
Of course. It's November 1st.
[HOTARO] So the crime was
committed yesterday,
October 31st, right?
Why didn't Shibazaki say,
"Kobundo next to the train
station yesterday,"
in his announcement?
Now that you mention it,
that is quite unusual.
Why would someone
spell out October 31st
instead of saying "yesterday"?
One explanation could
be that they have
some sort of form or
note in front of them
on which all that
is written out,
and they are reading the
date directly from it.
A form or a note, huh?
Yeah.
Furthermore, why do
the police know that X
was involved in a crime,
but have no idea
what X looks like?
Why would they assume
that X would come forward
just because they were paged?
To put it another way,
why would they think X felt
remorse for the crime?
It has to be that X sent an
apology note to Kobundo.
It probably went
something like this:
"I am terribly sorry.
I was shopping in your
store on October 31st
and committed an unlawful act.
I intend to pay for
the damage I caused,
so please accept such and such
and my sincere apology."
Kobundo then takes that apology
note directly to the police.
Either the police
or other law enforcement
follows up on the letter,
and decides to
come to Kami High.
That just happened,
mere moments ago.
Then Shibazaki reads the
note and is so outraged
that he makes a hasty
schoolwide announcement,
summoning the suspect
to the faculty room.
[ERU]
Hold on a minute.
Oreki, by your logic,
even though X wanted
to apologize to Kobundo
and repay them for the damage,
they hoped by writing the
letter that they could settle
without any police
involvement, right?
[HOTARO]
Yeah, that makes sense.
[ERU]
In that case, I don't think X
would have indicated
in their letter
that they were a student at
Kamiyama High, would they?
So then how would
the police have known
to look for them here?
Maybe when police asked
the owners of Kobundo
for a physical
description of the suspect,
they detailed X's clothes,
and police put together that it
was the uniform for Kami High.
That would be one
possible explanation.
[ERU]
Interesting.
[HOTARO] And if X did anything
that made them stand out,
it would make sense for the
owners to remember details.
What would make them stand out?
Well, let's see.
We might be able to
determine the crime from that.
So, X behaved oddly.
They did something outrageous
enough to attract attention,
but that's not
necessarily illegal.
Then X committed a crime,
the nature of
which is such that,
without the apology letter,
no one would have
known right away.
X was consumed with regret.
X's crime was serious
enough that it warranted
contacting law
enforcement immediately.
Whatever X did yesterday--
It wasn't something petty,
like shoplifting.
Then, what?
[HOTARO] Shopping in
a way that stood out.
Shopping that became illegal.
You said that Kobundo
is a stationery store
that caters to
grade school kids,
so it's not likely that they
carry anything of much value.
[HOTARO] Shopping...
shopping... shopping.
No way.
What is it?
[HOTARO]
Our friend, X,
tried to pay with a
counterfeit 10,000 yen bill.
But... But...
But that can't be true!
It's just way too far-fetched.
I don't think it's realistic!
It defies any sort of logic!
It's a terrible theory!
It's completely catastrophic!
[HOTARO]
Whoa. Hey.
Calm down.
[HOTARO]
This is just a game, you know?
Right. I'm sorry.
It's not real.
Don't take it so seriously.
I know, but still...
It's not possible...
It can't be.
Why are you so
sure it's impossible?
[ERU] It's been all over
the news that someone
has been trying to pass
off 10,000 yen bills.
That's what gave you the
idea in the first place:
That X must be someone
from our school
who tried to pay with one
of them yesterday, right?
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
But X could not have
possibly gotten ahold
of one of those counterfeit
bills, or even if they had,
they would have
realized it was fake
and handed it over
to the police.
[HOTARO]
What makes you say that?
[ERU]
Bear with me here.
Let's say X did
get a counterfeit bill.
Where do you think they
could have done that?
[HOTARO]
From an ATM, I would imagine.
Counterfeit bills
that are good enough
to slip past bank
tellers into an ATM
aren't very common.
And even if by some
chance that happened,
the bill would be so good
that X wouldn't spot it.
If X was given change--Oh.
That's right.
You can't get 10,000
yen bills as change.
Except for commemorative coins,
the 10,000 is the highest
note there is here.
I think I see what
you're getting at now.
That means there's only
one or two other ways
in which X could have acquired
a fake bill innocently.
But even if we assume X's
parents own their own business,
and had a counterfeit
bill given to them
without their knowledge,
if X had gotten it as
allowance or something,
X would have had the chance
to tell his or her parents
it was a fake.
[ERU]
I think you're right.
And if X had earned it at a
part-time job or something,
they would have had a chance
to turn it in then, as well.
What if X found it?
That would be too crazy!
Yeah, someone who would
find a counterfeit bill
and try to pass it off
as real doesn't seem like
the kind to write an
apology letter, do they?
X probably noticed
at the last minute
and felt guilty as they
were trying to pay with it.
Without knowing how X
obtained a counterfeit bill,
it's impossible to say whether
your deduction is realistic.
A 10,000 yen note.
Chitanda. Would you
say that you like money?
I'm not sure.
I suppose it's fair to say I
like it more than I dislike it.
If you dropped 10,000 yen,
would you miss it?
Yeah, of course I would.
Well... Unless I knew my money
wasn't the genuine article.
If it was your own, real money,
then I bet you would
miss it for sure.
The reason X felt guilty,
even while committing the crime,
is that it was their own money.
Even if it was a fake.
I submit that X must have
gotten that bill from someone,
thinking it was
legitimate currency,
and if that wasn't from
wages or allowance,
there's only one
other possibility.
Someone gave it to them
when they repaid a loan.
If X had gotten the
bill in that manner,
and discovered it was a fake,
they'd have been
really disappointed.
That being the case,
it's hard to blame them
for trying to use it at a store
run by an old man and woman.
Even if they knew it
was immoral to do that.
Even so, they still would
have had the opportunity
to turn it in and
exchange it for real money!
[HOTARO]
I don't know.
A fake bill is like
the joker in Old Maid.
No one wants to
get stuck with it.
You know, the longer
I think about this,
the more plausible
it sounds to me.
"Hey, X, I have the money
that I borrowed from you
a while back."
"Ah, Y, that's great.
I appreciate it."
"It was 10,000 yen, right?
Here ya go."
"Yes, thank you."
Then, surprise,
it's a fake bill.
Maybe Y, who borrowed
the money from X,
had seniority over X,
complicating things.
So X didn't feel like
they could object
when Y paid them back
with a counterfeit note.
At this point, I think
it's safe to say that X
is just one person.
And since Kobundo
is a store that sells
inexpensive stationery
for grade school kids,
it would be weird for
high schoolers to come in
buying things with
10,000 yen bills.
[HOTARO]
I think that wraps that up.
Then there's Y.
Y also came across a fake bill.
It could be that Z,
someone above Y,
gave it to them.
If we lump everyone
above Y together
as one collective,
then who are they?
A store manager somewhere
with no conscience,
or the counterfeiter themselves?
The police may have
gotten involved at Kami
in the hope that they
could find out from X
specifically where
the counterfeit bills
were originating.
That's my guess.
[HOTARO]
And that concludes my deduction.
Hmm...
After I talked for so long,
it seems kind of rude
of her not to respond.
Whatever.
[HOTARO] Kobundo is
over that way, isn't it?
[ERU]
That's amazing.
"Anyone who was
shopping at Kobundo
near the train station
on October 31st,
please report to Shibazaki in
the faculty room immediately."
A whole story. Wow.
Just from that one announcement.
Yeah, that's what
we came up with.
Game over, I guess.
Hey, Oreki.
Huh? What is it?
I seem to remember that
we started this whole game
as a way to settle an
argument we were having
about something.
Oh, that rings a bell.
Now what was it, again?
I can't recall.
Oh, Oreki... I have an idea.
Do you want to
deduce what it was?
[HOTARO]
Give me a break.
Whoa...
But that was
supposed to be a game.
I thought...
It couldn't possibly be true.
Hmm.
[ERU] Next time:
"Mishap-py New Year."