[EBA] Each of these three
has their own theory
about how the murder mystery
is supposed to play out
in the finished script.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd listen
to what they have to say and
then tell me what you think.
Sure!
[NAKAJO]
So, what's the deal?
You guys are mystery
experts or somethin'?
[EBA]
This is Junya Nakajo.
He's our assistant director.
And that's Tomohiro Haba.
The props master.
Nice to meet you.
[EBA]
Finally, we have...
Ciao, ciao!
[EBA]
Misaki Sawakiguchi. PR rep.
Thanks for coming all
the way to Class F!
This is gonna be awesome!
Yeah. Sure.
I'm kinda gettin' a weird
vibe from these three.
All right then--we'll
let you get started.
Have fun! We'll talk soon!
[HABA]
Hope it goes well.
Sorry we got even
more people dragged
into this mess.
The movie was a blast
when we first started out,
but without an ending,
we're kinda screwed,
so thanks a lot for helping.
Sure.
[ERU]
Oh, I almost forgot!
Here.
I brought these for
everyone to share.
What are they?
Whiskey-filled chocolates, huh?
Promotional samples of a
new product, apparently.
[HOTARO gags]
[ALL coughing]
Phew!
--[MAYAKA groaning]
--[HOTARO coughing]
That's strong!
[HOTARO grunts]
[NAKAJO]
Well, wanna get started?
Why don't you give
us your perspective
as a member of the film crew?
Would you say it was
a difficult shoot?
[NAKAJO] The performance
and production side of things
was pretty fun, actually.
It was just getting out there
that was a pain in the butt.
By bus and train, the trip
was more than an hour.
I mean, would it
have killed them
to choose someplace closer?
Why do think they
chose that location?
I guess someone
recommended it because
it had an interesting
look to it.
I've heard about
the deserted village
in the Narakubo area,
but I'm surprised
you were allowed to film there.
The person who
recommended it had an in
with the property manager.
What's this got to do
with anything, though?
You never know what
information might
hold an important clue.
Please, let's continue.
Actually, if you don't
mind me interrupting,
I'd love to know
how Hongo is doing.
Not very well
from the sound of it.
But honestly, I wasn't too
surprised when she got sick.
Why's that?
Is she the type of person who
gets sick a lot or something?
Yeah, she's been
absent from school
a whole bunch of times
throughout the year.
She didn't make it out
to the shoot, either.
[HOTARO] She worked
that hard on the script
but then didn't
come to the shoot?
[HOTARO] How did the crew
feel about Hongo's script?
Was it pretty well-received?
[NAKAJO]
Of course it was!
No one had any problems with it.
I mean, why would they?
[HOTARO]
You sound a little defensive.
I'm sorry. Did I hit a nerve?
[NAKAJO]
I'm not being defensive.
I'm just telling you that
everyone liked Hongo's script.
And that includes me!
[MAYAKA]
Ahem.
Let's move on to
a different question.
Uh-- Sure.
So did Hongo say anything
to the actors about
which of them might
be playing the murderer?
Hm... No, there's not really
anything I can think of.
Well, maybe...
[gasps]
It might not mean
anything, but I remember
she made a point to
wish Konosu good luck.
[HOTARO] Which she could
easily have said to anyone.
So then, have you interviewed
all the actors about this?
To see if Hongo
said anything to them
that might be helpful?
No, none of them.
As assistant director,
did you observe
anything else that
might be significant?
Significant, like how?
[MAYAKA groans]
Well. Questions over?
So maybe you'd like
to hear my theory
about the murderer now?
More than anything.
Ahem!
If you ask me, your
typical viewer doesn't care
about fancy plot devices.
All they want is a good story.
"That's him! He's the murderer!"
[NAKAJO]
Once his guilt is revealed,
the culprit breaks down
in tears and
confesses his crimes.
The mystery's solved,
and everyone goes home happy.
Uh...
[HOTARO]
Huh?
I think that's just the
sort of satisfying ending
the audience would expect
after the horrifying discovery
of Kaito's body. Our props
guy did a great job
with that scene.
Even on the fly.
[HOTARO]
"On the fly"?
You're saying the
scene was adlibbed?
[NAKAJO]
Yeah.
Everybody got all
fussy about it, though.
Goin' on about the
rules of a mystery.
It's the drama of the story
that matters, not the details!
I say play the title straight.
"The Case of the Furuoka
Deserted Village Murder."
Putting death right
there in the title
is a good way to sell seats.
I betcha Hongo knew that
much about mystery flicks.
Hm.
Okay, then.
Do you wanna tell us
your theory of the crime?
[NAKAJO]
Given the way he died, you know
what this was, right?
A locked-room murder.
Kaito was found in a
room with only one door,
and it was locked. So,
how'd the killer get out?
That's the real question here.
[MAYAKA] And... You think
you have an answer?
[NAKAJO]
Sure. It's simple.
Through the window.
[MAYAKA]
The window?
[NAKAJO]
Yeah.
The murderer kills Kaito
then climbs out the window.
It's pretty obvious
if ya think about it.
[HOTARO]
Hold on.
My memory's a little
bit fuzzy here.
Satoshi, you have the floorplan?
Yes, sir, I've got it right
here as a matter of fact.
There. Let's take a look.
[SATOSHI] This is the
room where Kaito died.
In the stage left wing.
The other characters
enter the room here,
through the right hallway.
Except initially,
the door was locked.
So two of the characters
head back down the hall
to get the master key.
[MAYAKA]
Then they return, open the door,
and find Kaito dead
inside the room.
There were two
other entry points,
but they were totally blocked
with furniture and other junk.
[SATOSHI]
So, as Nakajo suggested,
there were only two points
of access to the murder scene.
The door everyone
came in through,
and the window on this wall.
[ERU] Except, that doesn't
mean much of anything
if Hongo didn't know when
she wrote the script.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I just mean...
Well, uh...
You're totally right,
that's important.
[MAYAKA]
How do you figure?
What if she wrote
the script without
seeing the place?
If the story was based on
the floor plan alone,
she might have considered
other escape routes
for the murderer to have taken.
[NAKAJO]
She saw it.
Hongo went to visit
the shoot location
before she started
writing the script.
Do you know when
she went to see it?
[NAKAJO]
I think it was June.
No, maybe the end
of May, actually.
Is that so?
[NAKAJO]
So there ya go, right?
The killer came in and went
out through the window.
No need for a door at all.
Just climb in, do the deed,
and climb back out.
Mystery solved.
Boom!
[HOTARO gasps]
[HOTARO]
Really? "Boom"?
That works, but it wouldn't make
for a very well-crafted mystery.
Why would it be "well-crafted"?
It's not like Hongo was
an expert on mysteries.
It didn't really
seem like she had
anything fancy in mind.
Okay then, who's the killer?
What do you mean?
Even if we say your theory about
how it went down is true, can
you tell us who the killer is?
[sighs] Well...
You didn't take into
account the fact
that we get a look outside
the window after everyone
arrives at the scene, did you?
[NAKAJO]
Uh...
[MAYAKA]
The grass was way overgrown.
Anyone passing through
it would have left
a pretty obvious trail,
but from what I recall,
nothing looked like it was even
a little bit out of place.
That doesn't line up
with your theory.
The killer couldn't have
fled through the window.
I dunno--maybe Hongo forgot
to write that part in.
Now you're grasping at straws.
Come on. Hongo wasn't a slacker.
From what we've heard,
her writing was consistent.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Wait a sec! It's summer now!
Don't you get it?
Remember how I said that
Hongo went to scout out
the site back at the end of May?
Well, at that point in time,
the summer grass
hadn't grown in yet!
So she probably wouldn't
have taken the grass
into account when
she wrote the scene.
All we have to do is
cut the grass and re-shoot
the dead body scene,
then everything should fall
neatly into place,
top to bottom!
And there ya have it. Boom!
Ha...
See? We solved it!
The killer fled
through the window.
Now we can get back to
shooting and finish this movie.
Thanks! See ya later!
Huh...
You think he's right?
It's not much of a plot twist.
It isn't fancy. But it
is feasible at least.
[MAYAKA]
Feasible and lame.
[ERU]
Well, Oreki?
Do you think Nakajo's
theory is in line
with what Hongo
originally intended?
It doesn't sit right with you?
I wouldn't say that.
I...
I'm not totally
convinced, that's all.
[HOTARO] In other words,
it doesn't sit right with you.
Yeah.
Well,
I can definitely see flaws
in Nakajo's version of events.
Huh?
Would you care to elaborate?
What seems like
a simple solution
to the physical problem
of a locked room
is made problematic itself
by the psychology involved.
Say what now?
You think you could find a more
convoluted way of putting it?
Every bit the
cerebral detective.
[HOTARO]
Hmph.
Uh...
Would you mind explaining
what you meant, exactly?
Just that any killer
with an instinct
for self-preservation
wouldn't risk going in
through the window.
The window's here, right?
If you go in that way,
you're practically guaranteed
to be seen by somebody.
There are other windows
here, here, and here.
Walking around in broad
daylight, there's no way
you're going to go unnoticed.
[SATOSHI]
Good call.
If I were the killer,
that would probably be
the last way I'd go.
Well, that's my take, anyway.
[MAYAKA]
I get your point.
But did Hongo see the
same problems you did?
There's no way for us to know.
You may be right.
But I do think if we can
get our hands on a copy
of the script, that would
help us figure some stuff out.
[SATOSHI] I'm curious.
When it comes to mysteries,
what kind does everybody read?
Uh, why?
[SATOSHI]
I got to thinking while we were
listening to Nakajo talk.
He has his own idea
of what a "mystery"
should look like,
but what do we all think?
Nakajo's idea of a mystery
seems as sophisticated
as a kid's picture book.
[SATOSHI] Mm-hm. What kind
do you read, then?
Dunno.
Just the standard
bestsellers, really.
And you, Mayaka?
Old stuff. You know,
like Christie.
The classics, huh?
What about you, Chitanda?
I don't read them.
Seriously? Not at all?
It's not that I've
never read one,
it's just I haven't
bothered to in a long time.
The truth is, I don't really
care for mystery novels.
I guess I've read enough
of them to know that much,
at least.
That blows my mind.
Didn't see that one coming.
Okay, so what's your
mystery genre of choice?
Oh, me? Ah. Well, you know.
He may not wanna come
right out and say it,
but Fuku here fancies
himself to be a Sherlockian.
What? I've never heard
of a Sherlockian before.
[HOTARO]
From the name, I'd say it refers
to a passionate fan
of Sherlock Holmes.
Very passionate.
Seriously hardcore.
Right?
[SATOSHI laughs nervously]
I don't know if
that's really how
I would describe it.
You might be oversimplifying
a little bit.
[knocking]
Uh--
Did the interview go well?
Yeah. I guess.
We've rejected
Nakajo's idea, though.
Very well. I understand.
There's one other thing.
What is it?
You think you could get
us a copy of the script?
We'd like to get a better feel
for Hongo's attention to detail.
I'll see if I can find one.
It may take me some time.
While I'm looking, you can
speak with our props master,
Tomohiro Haba. He's
waiting just outside.
Hey there.
I understand the
four of you know
your mystery stories.
[HOTARO sighs]
[hiccups] Oh.
[HABA]
You know,
if you think of a mystery
as a contest between
author and reader,
an amateur writer like
poor Hongo is bound
to come up a little short.
[MAYAKA] We heard that she
didn't have a lot of experience
with the genre.
Yeah.
She used those
books to get ideas
for how to write the screenplay.
Until she started
working on this film,
I don't think she'd seen
any crime shows or movies
or read any mystery novels.
Oh, the Nobuhara translation.
Looks like the latest editions.
She was teaching
herself how to write
a mystery by reading
Holmes novels?
See what I mean?
Obviously, Hongo was
a total amateur.
[SATOSHI] I suppose you
could put it that way.
Hey, Oreki, look at this.
What is it?
There are some
strange looking marks
here on this paper. See?
Here's another one.
They're on here, too!
She probably just
marked the stories
she wanted to draw from.
You really think that's all?
[HABA]
Well, anyway...
When are we gonna
work on our own mystery?
[SATOSHI]
What is this?
[HABA]
A floorplan from town hall.
[SATOSHI]
Oh.
[MAYAKA] We're interested
to hear your theory.
Ahem.
If you want my
opinion, this mystery
is not especially
difficult to solve.
Not if you're experienced
with this sort of thing.
Is that so?
The first point I would
make is that the murder
was not premeditated.
Rather, circumstances simply
fell neatly into place,
and the killer seized
that opportunity to act.
Why do you say that?
Heh... It couldn't
have been pre-planned,
since there was no way
to guarantee Kaito
would end up in that room.
The keys were spread out
on the table, remember?
Everybody picked
one up at random,
and that's what decided
where they went to explore.
Now, then.
This is a locked-room
murder, right?
All points of escape
were effectively blocked,
aside from the window,
and the ground outside
of that showed no sign of
having been recently disturbed.
That tells us whoever
killed Kaito could not
have escaped using
conventional methods.
And of course, let's not forget
the question of how the killer
entered the room
in the first place.
Could they have used
the master key
and then replaced it afterwards?
That is clearly an
implausible explanation.
In order to get to the
office where the keys were,
they would have to risk passing
through the front lobby here.
That would put them
in danger of being seen
by any of the other characters
who were moving about
the building, so we can easily
write-off that possibility.
And the office isn't
the only area the killer
couldn't reach.
The first-floor hallway
down the right side
is the only open route
leading to the room
in which Kaito was found,
but none of the others
could have accessed it.
Can anyone tell us why?
For the same reason
you already gave.
They couldn't risk
walking through the lobby
and being seen by somebody.
[HABA]
A good deduction.
Plus, how could
someone reach that room
and still have time to re-enter
from the correct direction
when they regrouped?
So, other possibilities.
Perhaps Kaito's death
could have been a suicide
disguised to look like a murder?
Given the fact his
arm was taken off,
I'd say that's highly unlikely.
All in all, this could be
a difficult murder to solve.
At least, for someone
who doesn't have experience
with these things.
But not for you.
This is your specialty, right?
What do you think
the solution is
to this murder mystery?
Well, gosh.
I just don't know.
The mystery expert doesn't know!
Well, I suppose I can't
really blame you.
[HABA]
This is the key.
[SATOSHI]
Some rope?
I am the props master, remember?
And Hongo specifically
asked me to procure this.
She said we needed to find
a rope that was strong enough
that it could support
the full weight of a person.
I'm sure you can see where
this is leading, right?
Just think:
The killer couldn't enter
from the first floor,
but what about the second floor?
Konosu was the one
who went upstairs
to the right-hand hallway.
Konosu is in the
Mountaineering Club,
although you wouldn't know
it from looking at her.
She dangled the rope out
the second floor window,
climbed down it to the stage
left wing, killed Kaito,
then escaped using
the same route.
If I were going to decide
on a title for the movie...
Let me think.
I suppose I'd go
with something like
"The Unseen Incursion."
All right. I'm ready to
hear what you guys think.
[hiccups]
What other props were there?
Did Hongo ask for
anything interesting
besides the strong rope?
No, she didn't have
very many requests,
which I think speaks to
her lack of experience.
For example, the amount
of blood she asked for
wasn't nearly enough.
Fortunately, I had the
foresight to prepare extra
so we would have plenty on hand.
Now, will there
be anything else?
--If not, I'll just be goin--
--You know.
[HABA]
What is it?
[HOTARO] This may seem
like a silly question,
but have you seen the movie yet?
Actually, I haven't
had the chance to.
[MAYAKA]
That's it! Now I'm grouchy!
Yeah, 'bout what?
That guy's attitude.
I mean, he even made fun
of Sherlock Holmes.
Didn't that bother
you at all, Fuku?
Not really.
How could it not?
I think Sherlock Holmes
stories are perfect
for newcomers to
the mystery genre.
And that's exactly
what Hongo was,
so why shouldn't
she start there?
[MAYAKA grumbles]
So, what do we think
about Haba's conclusion?
Well...
It seemed like a
pretty good one to me.
I'm not saying I like the guy,
but there must be a reason
Hongo asked for rope,
and he makes a solid case
for his explanation.
Unfortunately, I can't
argue with it either.
[ERU]
I dunno.
I'm not completely
convinced that he's right.
Just like with
Nakajo's explanation--
I can't say what exactly,
but something about it
feels a little off to me.
I don't know, maybe
it's silly, but...
I don't think that's
what Hongo intended
when she was writing the script.
[HOTARO] You really put
down a lot of those.
Whoa!
[ERU]
Whoops! Did I eat all of them?
I couldn't decide
if I liked them,
so I kept trying them
to see if I could
make up my mind.
[MAYAKA]
How are you feeling, Chi?
Oh, I feel totally fine.
Pretty great, actually.
[ERU giggles]
Uh...
[ERU gasps]
Haba's theory!
Oreki, do you think he's
on the right track or what?
No, I think he's wrong.
[MAYAKA]
Why's that?
[HOTARO] It's not the idea
itself that's an issue.
That part's solid enough.
But it doesn't work in
this particular movie.
[SATOSHI]
Why not?
It's inconsistent with
what was filmed.
Oh. I see. The window, huh?
It probably hadn't
been opened in years,
since the place was abandoned.
Katsuta gave it a good pull
and it still
didn't wanna open,
so it must've been shut tight.
Plus, it creaked loudly
and opened upward.
It would be impossible
to open it quietly while
dangling from a rope.
Do we really think Kaito
would just stand there
doing nothing while somebody
was rattling at the window?
[SATOSHI]
That would pretty dumb.
That explains why you asked Haba
whether or not
he'd seen the movie.
[HOTARO] Hongo had gone there
to scope out the place.
If the window was such
an important plot point,
she would've checked to see
if it would open or not.
But we all saw
the footage, right?
Obviously, the state
of the window
wasn't a big concern for her.
[MAYAKA grumbles]
I can't believe I was so quick
to buy that jerk's idea!
[knocking]
How did it go this time?
[SATOSHI]
Rejected.
[EBA]
Very well.
[EBA] Here you are.
I've brought the script.
Thank you. This
should be helpful.
Hey, that looks cool!
Can I have one, too?
Tipsy, much?
I'm just fine, thank you.
Come on. Let us see.
[HOTARO] Looks pretty
well laid out to me.
She didn't skimp on details.
Look at this note: "Make sure
there are no footprints
outside the window."
[MAYAKA] Nakajo's theory
is totally out then.
There's still one person left.
Sawakiguchi, right?
[SAWAKIGUCHI]
Sorry, am I late?
Ciao!
Hello, there, Sawakiguchi!
I mean, "ciao"!
[SAWAKIGUCHI]
I'd love to get this sorted out.
There's not much I can do
on the publicity front
till we've got a title.
It's not like I can
start making posters
or anything. It's way
past time we get this whole
script thing settled,
if you ask me.
I've been wondering.
Did Hongo volunteer herself
to write the screenplay?
Nope. She was recommended.
And making the film a mystery?
Voted by the majority.
What about the idea
to make a movie--
I think we're getting
a little off track here.
I don't think so. I'm curious!
Here, I have the
meeting minutes.
If it'll help, you're
welcome to take a look.
[ERU]
Great, thank you!
All righty.
Is everybody ready to listen
to what I have to say?
First, I'd like to know what
you picture in your head
when you hear
the word "mystery."
Let's start with... this guy!
"Murder on the Orient Express"?
A boring old whodunit book?
How lame can you get?
Huh?
Think about what you see
if you're renting a movie.
It's all slasher flicks--the
kinda stuff that's full of blood
and gore and chainsaws.
You know what I mean?
Except those are horror films.
Yeah, sure, I know
what you mean.
Huh?
Think about it from
the perspective of someone
who's not all that
interested in the genre.
They wouldn't draw a distinction
between mystery and horror.
[SAWAKIGUCHI]
So anyway.
The problem is that no one
could get into the room
where Kaito died, right?
So obviously,
there must have been
a seventh person.
Um, what?
[SAWAKIGUCHI] Hongo was
looking for another actor,
in addition to the original six.
[MAYAKA, SATOSHI]
Huh?
Just think about it:
they all begin to suspect
one another.
And right about the
time their paranoia
starts to peak,
the phantom psycho killer
appears out of nowhere!
[HOTARO]
Hm?
Phantom killer?
[BOTH scream]
[SAWAKIGUCHI] I'm not sure how
many of them get killed off,
but I think the best bet is
to have one couple left alive,
y'know, for a little romance.
Together, they're able
to defeat the phantom.
And they share
a kiss at sunrise.
As for the title...
"Bloody Beast" would work.
Or whatever. That might
be a bit cheesy.
So, what do you think?
Good story, right?
[MAYAKA]
Except...
The room where Kaito
died was locked.
So how did the killer get out?
Isn't it obvious?
He's a phantom.
[MAYAKA, SATOSHI gasp]
[SAWAKIGUCHI] Phantom killers
can walk through walls,
can't they? But if
that doesn't work...
I know!
It could be a vengeful spirit!
Yeah! That's even better!
[ERU]
She's totally, completely wrong!
There's no way that's
how Hongo meant
for it to end when
she wrote the screenplay!
Gettin' a little worked up.
I agree, though, that sounds
more like a bad joke
than a movie.
But technically speaking,
it would fit
with what's been filmed so far.
It's wrong. Just wrong!
Yeah, maybe. But can
you disprove it?
What's wrong is wrong. The end!
[gasps]
You okay?
It's like looking
into a kaleidoscope.
What do you mean?
Hey! Can you hear me?
Hello?
[MAYAKA]
I think she's asleep.
[SATOSHI]
I have to admit...
Sawakiguchi's idea
may have been crazy,
but I kinda liked that about it.
To be honest,
I sorta like it, too.
I'll bet you do.
There are some
inconsistencies, though.
Like what?
We all saw how
detailed the script was.
If Hongo had been planning
that kind of horror twist
for the second half of it,
she would have arranged
for the necessary props,
don't you think?
One prop in particular.
And what would this
particular prop be?
You know.
The one Haba had the
foresight to make lots of.
Oh.
[HOTARO] Hongo only asked for
a small amount of fake blood.
The description in the
script seems to back that up.
Knowing that, we can
assume she wasn't planning
on a movie with
a high body count.
[SATOSHI]
I buy it.
Not much of a horror movie
with only one dead person.
[MAYAKA] It's starting to
feel like we're never going
to figure this out.
[knocking]
[door scrapes]
What did you think
of this theory?
Rejected again.
[MAYAKA] Come on, Chi,
let's get you home.
[ERU]
I'm sorry about this.
[MAYAKA]
Uh--
[SATOSHI] Three possible
endings, but none of 'em work.
I wonder what's gonna
happen to their movie now.
[HOTARO] Well, they won't be
able to finish it, will they?
Kinda depressing, isn't it?
"Summer grass,
'tis all that remains
of ancient warriors' dreams."
[HOTARO]
Mm.
[SATOSHI]
Later.
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
Oh, my god!
I can't believe that!
[IRISU] No matter how much
passion goes into a film,
without real skill,
it feels amateur.
[GIRL 9A]
Totally.
[GIRL 9B]
Yeah, I know, right?
And I haven't even told
you the best part yet.
Hello.
I wonder if you might
have time for a cup of tea.
[HOTARO]
Next time: "Blind Spot to All."