It was clever to
have the camera man
be the seventh character.
And I thought the
scene where the other six
looked into the camera
at the same time
had a lot of impact.
But still...
The rope didn't figure into your
new conclusion in any way!
[HOTARO]
Well, yeah, but...
What makes you think the rope
was even part of the setup?
[MAYAKA]
It had to be!
Hongo insisted they find a rope
that could hold a
person's full weight!
Why would she do that if it
wasn't a part of her plan?
I'm sorry, I guess I could
be mistaken about that part.
Anyway, I thought
your idea turned out
to be really entertaining,
and the end caught everyone
totally by surprise.
I just thought it didn't fit
with the rest of the film,
if you want my honest opinion.
Yeah.
Well, I'd better get
going to Manga Club.
See you tomorrow, Oreki.
[HOTARO] How could I have
forgotten about the rope?
Did I ignore it?
Not intentionally.
Did I twist the narrative
to make it fit Kaito better?
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro!
Hotaro! Hey, wait up!
[HOTARO gasps]
Whoa, are you okay?
Yeah, it's nothing.
What's going on?
Oh, I wanted to talk
to you about something.
Where's Mayaka?
[HOTARO]
She had to go to Manga Club.
[SATOSHI] Good, I'm
actually glad it's just us.
Did Chitanda have to leave, too?
Yeah, she did.
Why? Do you not
want them to overhear
what you need to
discuss with me?
It's nothing major,
but I would prefer to talk
about it with you in private.
Right. So what's up?
It's about the film's ending.
Was the plot twist
part of Hongo's plan?
Or did you come up with
all of that on your own?
It was Hongo's idea.
Okay.
I would be lying to you
if I said I believed
the ending was Hongo's idea.
I don't know what
she intended to write,
but I am positive
that wasn't it.
Are you basing that
on something specific?
Yeah.
How could I have
missed an inconsistency
so glaring that two people
picked up on it?
[SATOSHI]
There's no inconsistency.
I really thought
it was fantastic.
But it wasn't keeping
in line with the story
she wanted to tell.
Meaning what?
Have you ever heard of
the term "narrative trick"?
Isn't that a way of
fooling the reader
with clever storytelling?
[SATOSHI]
That's right.
The surprise twist of the
murderer being the camera man
in this film is a
perfect example.
[HOTARO]
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Do you remember our
conversation about the books
Hongo used to study
the mystery genre
in preparation for
writing this script?
Sherlock Holmes , right?
Exactly, she didn't
read anything other
than Sherlock Holmes .
That's telling, and here's why.
Doyle didn't use
narrative tricks
in the Sherlock Holmes novels.
[HOTARO gasps]
[SATOSHI]
Except for a handful of cases,
narrative tricks weren't in use
until Agatha Christie's era,
which wasn't until the
mid-1920s at the earliest.
Now, I don't know Hongo at all.
But I find it hard to
believe she'd be on par
with Agatha Christie!
Personally, the movie turned
out to be right up my alley.
And if it was all your idea,
I promise not to say anything!
But if you're trying to
pass it off as Hongo's work,
I have to tell you
that you're wrong.
Hold on a second!
We don't have some
comprehensive list
of everything she's read!
Maybe she learned to
use narrative tricks
by reading about them
in some other book!
Hell, maybe she even
saw one used in a movie!
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro!
Is that what you
actually believe?
If it is, and you feel
like you made the right call,
then I'll let this go.
That's all I wanted
to talk to you about.
I gotta go. I'll see you around.
Hey, what's wrong?
I thought you would've
already gone home by now.
[ERU]
Listen, Oreki.
There's something I
wanted to talk to you about.
Oh, great. You, too?
[HOTARO] This is about
Class 2-F's movie, isn't it?
[ERU]
Yes.
[HOTARO]
So you didn't like it?
[ERU]
No, it's not that at all.
[HOTARO]
You can be honest.
Satoshi and Ibara already
talked to me about it.
They said they knew it
wasn't what Hongo intended.
And, well...
I'm beginning to think
you guys are right.
I don't think it
was what she wanted.
[HOTARO sighs]
And what makes you
say that, specifically?
It's still pretty early, huh?
Do you wanna take a walk
with me down by the river?
So, Oreki, do you
know what it was
that made me so curious
about all of this
in the first place?
How I was gonna tie up
all the loose ends
and wrap the movie, right?
That's why you came to watch it.
No, I didn't really
have any interest
in how the movie
was going to end,
to be perfectly honest.
That's why I told you that
the idea you came up with
was such a brilliant one.
Then what were you
so curious about?
Well...
I was actually more interested
in Hongo as a person, you know?
I thought the
whole script thing
was really bizarre
from the beginning.
Why didn't Irisu talk to someone
who was close to Hongo?
Eba knows Hongo really well,
so she could have
helped Irisu figure out
how Hongo wanted
the movie to end.
And it would have
been a lot easier.
And Hongo still would
have been able to rest,
you mean?
[HOTARO] If you've got something
in mind, you should say it.
I think Hongo had a
clear vision of her script
from the beginning,
right up to the very end.
Even if she had gotten sick
in the middle of things,
they could have
asked her about it.
And if she was too
frail to handle that,
I would think Eba would have
gotten so mad at the class
she wouldn't have participated.
She would have been furious!
And she probably
wouldn't have escorted us
to the detectives.
You're right.
Did Hongo really not tell
anyone else in the class
how the rest of
her film played out?
Are you implying
that Hongo still wanted
to write the rest
of the script herself?
No. from the way
Eba described her,
I get the impression Hongo's
too meek to insist on it.
I don't think that kind
of girl would have the gall
to keep her
classmates waiting around.
Well...
Maybe she didn't have
confidence in her conclusion.
That's an option
I've considered, as well.
But the other kids in the
class seem like nice people.
I don't think they would be
disrespectful of her idea,
or insult her or anything.
[HOTARO]
Nice people, huh?
If the ending you wrote is
the one she came up with,
I'm sure she would have
had enough confidence in it
to share it with the others.
It was that great of an idea.
But I don't think she came up
with something that good,
so she kept quiet.
And if all that's true,
what was it that pushed her
to the point of
not finishing it?
That's what I have to find out!
I believe that
all of her regrets,
how she really felt about
not being able to finish
what she started,
all those screams of frustration
were hidden in the script!
The version that we
ended up with didn't have
any of her real
feelings left in it.
So if it seems to you like
I didn't enjoy the movie,
well, that's the
only reason why.
[HOTARO] While I was
busy trying to figure out
the puzzle of the film,
Chitanda was actually
concerned about Hongo.
What does that say about me?
I saw the script
as a literary problem,
and forgot about the
human side of things.
The theatre setting.
The cast of characters.
The gruesome murder.
The setup.
The killer....
lurks among you all undetected!
[AUDIENCE claps, cheers]
[HOTARO] I never even
considered that Hongo
could have written her
feelings into the script
as some hidden code.
[HOTARO]
Pathetic. Some detective I am.
I'm not saying that you did
anything wrong at all, Oreki.
The last scene was really
quite a shock to everyone!
It may not have been what
Hongo originally intended,
but at the end of the day
it was a great ending.
[HOTARO] I wasn't asked to come
onboard as a screenwriter.
[HOTARO] I did a great job
if my assignment was
to screw things up.
But where did I go wrong?
[HOTARO] I can't wrap
my brain around it.
No lucky flashes of insight.
Who cares, anyway?
They already wrapped the film.
No matter how hard
I think about it,
it won't change anything.
Dwelling on it now is
just a waste of time
and precious energy.
[HOTARO]
Dammit!
[grunts]
[HOTARO] Maybe I'll read a book
to take my mind off of it.
[HOTARO]
A Tarot book?
I didn't know Sis
was into this stuff.
[HOTARO]
Let's see.
"The Empress.
Maternal affection,
a fertile mind, sensitivity."
From what I've seen, that
doesn't seem like Irisu at all.
So Ibara was "Justice."
"Equality, righteousness,
fairness."
Yep, that's not too far off.
Satoshi was "The Magician."
"Initiative, originality,"
and "interest," huh?
Interesting, indeed.
And Chitanda was "The Fool."
"Curiosity, impulse to action."
Sounds about right.
Okay, my turn.
"Inner fortitude,
fighting spirit, bonds?"
What the heck? That doesn't
sound like me at all!
Why would Satoshi
pick this for me?
"Strength is represented by
a picture of a ferocious lion
being controlled
by a kind woman."
What?
No way, I am not controlled
by women in any way!
Not my sister, Chitanda, Irisu,
or any of the rest of 'em.
Psh.
[HOTARO]
I dunno, maybe I am "Strength."
It's pretty fascinating.
Is he using the Tarot to hint
at some kind of judgment
he has of me?
That would be just like Satoshi.
It's not like he could
change my point of view.
Change my point of view?
Hey, there.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
[HOTARO]
Yeah, hi.
The class film turned out
quite well, don't you think?
We couldn't have done
it without you, so thanks.
Listen, there's a launch
party this Saturday.
Do you think you can come?
We'd all love to see you there.
I'm not coming.
Irisu, look.
I'd like to discuss something.
[WAITRESS 10A] One Yunnan
tea for the gentleman.
One green tea for the lady.
Please enjoy!
So what did you
want to discuss?
Do you remember the
last time we were here,
when you said that I was
gifted, a "true genius?"
Of course I do.
Just what did
you mean by that?
It's ironic that you don't know.
I was talking about--
You're lying to me!
I wasn't your detective.
I was your mystery writer.
Wasn't that your plan all along?
What gave my plot away?
Sherlock Holmes did.
Do you care if I spoil some
of his stories for you?
No, I don't mind at all.
I found some notes
tucked into the novels
that Hongo read to prepare.
I copied a few of
them down for you.
At first glance,
I assumed she had just
written them down as ideas
she might use in her script.
But unfortunately,
I was mistaken.
From what Satoshi told me,
"The Red-Haired League"
and "The Three Garridebs"
have pretty much
the same plot line.
So why did she mark, "The Red-
Haired League" with a triangle,
but "The Three Garridebs"
with a double-circle?
I talked it over with Satoshi,
and I realized that the
stories with double circles
are the ones in which
the characters survive.
In the ones marked
with an "X," they die.
Here's my hypothesis.
Hongo wasn't thinking about the
plotlines when she marked them.
She preferred happy endings
to tragedies. That's all.
She just couldn't stomach
it when people died.
Once I thought of it
in those terms,
several puzzles suddenly
made sense to me.
First, the small amount
of blood used.
Second, the unexpected
outcome of the questionnaire.
What are you talking about?
[IRISU] How were you able
to get your hands on this?
[HOTARO] All I had to do
was ask if I could borrow it.
So, as far as the
answers are concerned,
staging a hundred murders in
the film would be impossible.
'Cause there are only
about 30 kids in the class.
But some joker
still voted for it.
So what about this
other single vote, here?
A lone vote for having
zero murders in the film.
And that was how Hongo
cast her vote, wasn't it?
She didn't want
anyone to have to die
in the script she wrote at all.
Quite impressive.
However...
Her impulsive classmates decided
to improvise the violence.
I heard that Hongo didn't
even come to the shoot.
The strangest part is
that the script never says
that Kaito dies from his injury.
But in the film he does.
Yes, that's correct.
And that arm was
remarkably well-made.
[HOTARO]
Ibara mentioned that, too.
But Kaito died, any way you
slice it, no pun intended.
[HOTARO] From here out,
my statements are conjecture.
I have no hard evidence.
Regardless, I have no
choice but to say this to you:
Hongo didn't have the nerve
to stand up for her script
and demand the class
reshoot without the changes.
She was much too timid
to speak up that way.
I think she had some guilt about
ignoring the death toll tally
from the questionnaire.
But you decided to take
matters into your own hands.
The way things were going, Hongo
was becoming the class villain.
You set her up to come
down with an illness
and leave her script unfinished.
Then you rallied her
classmates together
and held a meeting
of collective deduction.
But in reality it was just
a scriptwriting contest.
Once you realized they couldn't
write to your standards,
you dragged us into it, too.
It's pathetic.
No one caught on to the
fact that they were doing
your dirty work, not even me!
That's because you had
manipulated our point of view.
Then, you replaced
her script with my work,
and she couldn't claim
that you hurt her.
She couldn't substantially
prove you did anything wrong!
Isn't that right?
I don't dispute any
of these accusations.
[HOTARO] You said something
else to me before...
That when people have talent
and can't recognize it,
they unknowingly hurt
those who don't have any.
That was just a tactic.
You don't truly care about
the feelings of people
who don't have
natural abilities.
All that really matters
to you is the bottom line.
Am I mistaken?
Is there something
wrong with that?
Fine, then!
When you told me I was special,
was that just so you
could manipulate me, too?!
When you said it's
right to acknowledge
who you really are,
you were thinking
of your own selfish interests!
Well, I was not being
completely sincere.
And if you choose to
call it an outright lie,
that's your choice.
[HOTARO] I'm not sure why,
but that's a relief.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You just have to know
what kind of script
Hongo actually
intended to write.
Is that what's twirling around
inside your head over there?
Huh? No, it's not that at all.
So what, then?
This isn't like you, y'know.
No, it's not like me.
You're right.
But I gotta say...
You're not acting quite like
yourself, either, Oreki.
[HOTARO]
Not like myself?
What's that mean?
Well, why don't I
just ask, like usual?
I'm curious.
What kind of script
did Hongo originally
dream up for the class film?
Please tell me.
I have to know, Oreki!
Ugh, your guess
is as good as mine.
Knowing Kaito's supposed to live
solves the locked-room problem.
Konosu is the real attacker,
and the entry point
was the window.
Huh? But I thought the window--
[HOTARO] I mean the window in
the stage right sitting room.
There are two, but it
doesn't matter which.
Konosu snuck in using
the rope Hongo asked for,
chased Kaito, and sliced him up.
Just one strike, though,
not enough to kill him.
Then she climbed back up
to the second floor,
using the same rope,
and met up with the rest of
the cast, looking nonchalant.
And that's that.
Ah, that must be why Hongo
wished Konosu luck, then.
It makes more sense now.
But wait...
What about the seventh character
Hongo was trying to cast?
[HOTARO] Yeah, they
turned up in the film,
even in the unfinished version.
[ERU]
They did?
Only the original six showed
up in the version that I saw.
[HOTARO] The cast didn't just
consist of the people onscreen.
There was a narrator, too.
Oh, right, I remember!
So why was the door
to the room the other six
found Kaito in locked, then?
Kaito went into the stage
left wing by himself,
and locked the door behind him.
[ERU]
Why would he do that?
Normally, I'd say "to stop
the murderer from getting him,"
but I don't think
that's the case here.
[ERU gasps]
What is it?
Oh, I just had the
realization that I understand
Hongo's intentions
a little bit better now.
Interesting.
[ERU] I bet that after
Konosu cuts Kaito,
she stays around for a minute,
and Kaito asks her
why she stabbed him,
because he's baffled by it.
Then, to cover for her,
for whatever reason,
he sends her back upstairs,
makes his way to
the stage left wing,
and collapses to the ground.
But then, how would
he explain away
the fact that he's
been cut that badly?
The injury could be
accounted for pretty easily,
because of the glass that
was all over the floor
in the room.
Oh, right, that
makes perfect sense!
[HOTARO]
He could just say that he fell
on a piece of the broken
glass and cut himself.
So that's how she
wanted the story to go?
Yeah, but we still don't know
why Konosu stabbed
Kaito in the first place,
or what made him decide
to forgive her, either.
Unless Hongo talks,
we might never find out.
I guess we'll leave it at that,
but why would anyone want to
stab one of their classmates,
and why would the
one who was stabbed
let their attacker
get away with it?
I'm dying to know why
Hongo was trying to depict
that scenario in
the first place.
By the way...
What is it?
Did you happen to know
more about this incident
than what you're
letting on here?
What? No, I didn't
know anything about it.
What would make you think I did?
You weren't convinced by any of
the other
detectives' hypotheses,
which is kind of out
of character for you,
so I wondered.
Was your empathy for Hongo
really the only reason?
Oh, yeah, I get that.
So listen...
If I tell you,
promise not to laugh!
Okay.
I think that Hongo and I are
really similar in a lot of ways.
Wow, this is a lot more
embarrassing than I thought.
The truth is...
I don't handle it very well
when characters have to die
in movies, either.
That is just like you.
[SATOSHI] Next time: "Those
Things Piled Up Endlessly."