[Bach's Cello Suite No. 1 plays]
[HOTARO groans lightly]
[HOTARO yawns]
Is that you, Sis?
[TOMOE] Guess who's
finally ho-oome?
[TOMOE chuckles]
I expect a big "welcome back"
hug when I come out.
I think I'll pass.
[TOMOE] After I've
been away for so long?
What a heartless little brother!
[HOTARO]
Hm.
Is this a souvenir
from South America?
[TOMOE] Sure is.
You wanted one, right?
No, not really.
[WEATHER GIRL] Good morning!
If you're just tuning in,
we're about to move on to
the national weather forecast.
[TOMOE] This is unusual.
Since when do you watch TV?
What about the paper?
[HOTARO] I don't feel
like working my brain.
[TOMOE]
Hmm.
[WEATHER GIRL] We'll see it
sweep across the country
from west to east
over the next few hours,
clearing up cloudy skies
as it pushes through.
[TOMOE] Your calendar
looks pretty empty.
[HOTARO] My schedule
is packed full.
[TOMOE]
Oh, yeah? Doing what?
[HOTARO]
Napping.
I know about a job
where you can get paid
for just sitting there
all day long. Want it?
[HOTARO]
Mmm.
[TOMOE] Well?
You interested?
[HOTARO]
Mmm.
[TOMOE] That sounds
like a "yes" to me.
I'll let them know
to expect you.
[WEATHER GIRL] Taking a look
at our extended forecast,
you'll see that as
we enter September,
the mornings will
finally cool off...
[TOMOE]
Here.
You're going to need this.
[phone rings]
[TOMOE]
Yes, Oreki residence?
Oh, hi Satoshi!
It's been a long time, huh?
Yeah. I just got back.
Hotaro? Sure, he's here.
Hold on a sec, 'kay?
Hotaro! Satoshi's on
the phone for you.
[HOTARO]
Mmm.
[SATOSHI] Hey. You know that
book I lent you last week?
You done reading it yet?
[HOTARO]
Mmm.
[SATOSHI]
Is that a "yes"?
'Cause if you are,
I'd like to get it back.
[HOTARO]
Mmm.
[SATOSHI] So, can I
come pick it up today?
Mmm. Just stop by
after I get off work.
[SATOSHI]
Huh?
After I get off work.
[SATOSHI] A job?
You have a job?
I don't understand.
What's going on?
[HOTARO] It's no big deal.
I'm just filling in
as a lifeguard over
at the municipal pool
for somebody my sister knows.
[SATOSHI] Ahh. Your sister.
That explains it.
Still, the thought of you doing
actual work boggles the mind.
[HOTARO] Well, anyway,
I've got to get going.
[SATOSHI] All right.
Maybe I'll stop by the pool
for a swim later.
[HOTARO]
Suit yourself. See ya.
[SATOSHI]
Bye.
[children laugh]
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro!
Hey! How's it going?
[ERU giggles]
[HOTARO] I didn't
realize all three of you
were going to show up.
I called the ladies right
after we got off the phone.
I said if they came with me,
they'd see a truly
exceptional sight.
Yeah, you did.
So where is it, then?
Right there!
The elusive Working Hotaro.
I gotta tell you,
I'm a little underwhelmed.
Not me! We all get to hang
out at the pool together.
I think this is going to be fun!
Yeah. You're right.
Let's make the best of it.
[ERU laughs]
[MALE VOICE]
Hey, you creep!
Unless you're
looking for trouble,
you better keep
your eyes off my girl!
Calm down.
He wasn't doing anything.
Yeah, I was
just standing here.
Sir, please take it easy,
or I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
What's all that about?
[HOTARO] Whatever's going on, I
just hope I can stay out of it.
[MOTHER] Come on,
sweetie, you can do it!
[KID]
Catch!
Are you ready, Mayaka?
It's coming your way!
And... go!
Here!
[SATOSHI grunts]
It's all yours.
You can do it!
Spike that ball!
Huh? Spike? I... Oh!
[MAYAKA laughs]
That was a pretty sad showing.
Right! Penalty game!
You know what to do.
[ERU sighs]
Ah! I'm sorry!
They made me!
[SATOSHI and MAYAKA laugh]
You watching?
[SATOSHI]
Whoo!
[BOTH]
Ready, set...
Here we go!
[MAYAKA and ERU
laugh and squeal]
[SATOSHI chuckles]
[SATOSHI]
All right, get ready!
Here... I... come!
Wooohoohoo!
[MAYAKA and ERU laugh]
[MAYAKA] You think
you're funny, don't you?
[HOTARO sighs]
[LIFEGUARD]
Hey!
Time to switch up. You can
take your lunch break now.
[ERU]
Hey, Oreki.
We were going to eat too,
if you'd like to join us.
If I'd had a little more
warning, I could've made
something a lot better
than this for lunch,
but I guess it'll have to do.
Hey, don't look at me.
This one's all on Hotaro.
Yeah, why do you say that?
He's a monument to idleness!
Look in the dictionary and
you'll see his picture next to
the word. Then out of nowhere,
he suddenly decides to
start earning a living.
He should've told us
about it immediately.
Really. Why didn't you?
[ERU]
Heh...
Well, anyway. I'm glad we
all got together like this.
It's been a lot of fun!
Mm. Totally.
I have to say, though, it's
not exactly a perfect match.
What's not a perfect match?
[SATOSHI]
The pool and Hotaro.
[MAYAKA chuckles]
That's for sure.
Come on, you two,
that's not very nice.
[MAYAKA] Swimsuits and Oreki
don't go together either!
Yep! The sun and Hotaro, there's
another bad match for ya.
[MAYAKA laughs]
The sea and Oreki!
How about summer
and Hotaro?
Okay, enough already.
Tell them to stop, Oreki.
[HOTARO]
Hm.
[SATOSHI] All right. Anybody
else wanna get back in the pool?
Sounds good to me. I'll take
care of throwing out our trash.
I have a few more bites,
but when I'm done,
I'll put our chairs back.
There we go.
[BOY cries]
[ERU gasps]
Aww. One ice cream
wasn't enough, huh?
Well, you certainly do have
a sweet tooth, don't you?
All right, you win.
Let's go and get you another.
That startled me
for a second.
Yeah.
So, are you liking
the job so far?
Sure. It's okay.
I've always wondered what
being a lifeguard was like.
[ERU gasps]
Look how fast they are!
I wonder if they're training
to be competitive swimmers
when they get older.
You never know, one of
them might even win
a gold medal at
the Olympics someday.
[HOTARO]
Yeah, maybe.
[ERU]
Huh?
It all just comes down to
what kind of person they are.
You know what I mean?
If they're special,
they'll do something great.
If they're average, they'll
just lead an average life.
And what about you? Have you
ever wanted to be special?
Not really. I'm just
a regular guy,
and that's all right with me.
That's not true. You are
special! To me, anyway!
[HOTARO]
Huh?
And the same thing goes
for Fukube and Mayaka.
You might not think of
yourselves as being special,
but I do because
you're my friends!
I'm not talking about
subjective opinions.
Objectively speaking, I'm not--
My opinion should count too!
I don't think it's a simple
matter of looking around
and categorizing everyone
as either special or average.
There's more to life than that.
As long as there's someone,
even just one person,
who thinks you're special,
I think that means you are!
Oh. I'm sorry. I just, uh...
I should get going.
[CHILD]
Ha ha ha! Wait up!
[ERU laughs]
That's not true.
You are special!
My opinion should count too!
[ALL THREE laugh]
Okay, Oreki.
It's your break time.
I'll take over here
for a little bit.
[ERU] So...
Are you on break?
[HOTARO]
Mm.
Well, um... There's something
that I'm sort of curious about.
[HOTARO]
Huh?
Yeah, it has to do with
the serious business
of lifeguarding.
[ERU] You see the
woman over there--
the one in the red swimsuit?
[HOTARO]
Mm.
[ERU] She's the same
one we saw earlier
when we were finishing lunch.
I remember that she had
something white on her ear.
But then I looked at her again
just now, and it's not there.
I'm surprised you noticed
something that tiny.
[ERU] I notice little things
about people sometimes.
I don't know why.
So? Why ask me about it?
Well, as one of the pool's
lifeguards, we thought
you'd be concerned about
the potential safety hazard.
If there's an earring
lying around out there,
someone could step
on it and get hurt.
[pop]
So, anyway. I thought maybe
you could look for it with us.
[HOTARO] Find one earring
in a place like this?
Is she kidding?
And you're sure you saw
something on her ear earlier?
Yes.
Even so, before we
start an all-out search,
maybe we should
verify that with her.
[I thought of doing
that, but, well...
I'm worried that
I'll get yelled at.
All you're doing is
asking about an earring.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Then how about
you go and ask her?
Thanks, I'm good.
[MAYAKA]
Hmph.
Please, I'd
appreciate it so much!
[MAYAKA] Come on.
Isn't this a lifeguard's job?
[SATOSHI] Well?
What do you say?
[HOTARO sighs]
Please help!
I have to know!
[HOTARO gasps]
[HOTARO sighs]
[CHIEF LIFEGUARD]
Huh?
That jerk from before?
I don't wanna get him
riled up again, y'know?
Yeah.
Tell ya what, I don't want to
turn this into a big deal.
So let's look for it discreetly.
Sure. It'll be slow-going
alone, though.
[CHIEF LIFEGUARD]
Right.
Well, you're not the only
lifeguard we have.
I'll get the others
to check the poolside.
As for you... you can
start inside the pool.
'Kay.
Don't worry. I'll help look.
Yeah, same goes for me.
Well...
Guess I'm in too, then.
Okay, thanks.
All right everybody,
what's the best way
to start looking for it?
Our best bet's probably to
split the place into sections.
Good idea. What do
you think of that, Oreki?
Knock yourselves out.
Seriously, would it kill you
to show a little initiative?
You're the lifeguard here,
so that means you should
be the one in charge.
Just assign us to
different parts of the pool.
[HOTARO]
Mmm.
Okay, fine, I'll take
care of it then. So...
Chitanda and Mayaka,
you two have the stair area.
Hotaro gets the slide area. And
I'll take the diving board area.
Well? Sound okay?
Yes, leave it to us!
Sure, why not?
Whatever.
Just curious...
[HOTARO]
Hm?
Why did you take this job?
Did you owe your big
sister or something?
No, I just took it.
That's not really staying
true to your motto.
What happened to "If I don't
have to, I'm not going to"?
What's it matter to you?
All right! Better!
I'm glad to get a reaction
out of you finally,
even if it is a pissy one.
Much less boring.
[HOTARO]
Ah...
See ya. Happy hunting.
[MAYAKA]
Oreki!
Doesn't look like you're
working very hard.
I'm pulling my weight.
I just found something
at the bottom of the pool
and came to throw it away.
Sure you did.
[MAYAKA sighs]
You know what? Just looking
at you right now is enough
to drain all my energy. I'm
practically falling asleep here.
So stop looking at me.
I'm used to being annoyed or
exasperated when I look at you.
This is different, though.
[MAYAKA] Either way, you're a
real pain most of the time.
But do us all a favor.
Go back to being the kind
of pain you used to be.
You're a lot more fun to be
around when you actually talk.
More fun to be
around... Huh?
[HOTARO gasps]
[MAYAKA]
Any luck?
No, none. But...
I don't think we need to
keep looking anymore.
Ah! I know what
that means, Hotaro.
You've figured it out,
haven't you?
[ERU gasps]
[HOTARO] Yeah.
I think I've got it.
Chitanda.
Are you sure it was an earring
you saw the woman wearing?
Am I a hundred percent sure?
I guess not. All I can say
for certain is there was
something white on her left ear.
[MAYAKA] What else
could it be, though?
There's no other jewelry you
wear on your ears, is there?
[HOTARO] Right.
That's what I'm wondering:
what else could it be?
What if we assume it wasn't
actually jewelry to begin with?
What? Now you've lost me.
Look at what she's
doing right now.
If she were wearing
anything in her ears,
would she be smacking
them like that?
Sounds like it would be
kind of painful to me.
[SATOSHI]
What's your point?
[HOTARO] I would guess
that whatever she had
on her ear was probably
something that got there
without her even knowing it.
[MAYAKA] All right, then. What
do you think it could've been?
[HOTARO]
That's the question.
Satoshi. Would you do me
a favor and pick Ibara up?
Sure.
[MAYAKA]
Mm...
No! I don't want him to.
All right, what if
Chitanda does it?
That's not gonna make it
any less embarrassing.
I don't wanna be picked up like
I'm some little kid, okay?
[HOTARO]
Well, that's a shame.
Since seeing a little kid picked
up is exactly what I'm after.
Why do you want somebody to
pick me up in the first place?
'Cause I'm trying
to prove a theory.
About whatever was
on the woman's ear?
Yeah.
[MAYAKA]
Hm...
I'm game if you are.
What can it hurt?
Eh...
Ah, all right, you win.
I'll sacrifice my dignity.
[MAYAKA gasps]
Impressive, Chitanda. I didn't
know you were so strong.
[MAYAKA] What's that
supposed to mean?
Whoa, hold on! I didn't
mean it that way, I swear.
It was just, y'know, a general
observation, that's all.
Yep. It fits.
What fits? Were you able
to prove your theory?
[HOTARO] It's her hand. She's
resting it on your shoulder.
So... Can she stop
holding me now?
Yeah. I've seen enough.
[ERU]
Down you go.
Look over there
for a second.
[HOTARO] Earlier, I saw
the woman in the red suit
holding that kid. Exactly the
way Chitanda was holding Ibara.
If he was eating an ice cream
cone like that at the same time,
what would've happened?
[SATOSHI] I get it!
The cone would've been
at the perfect height to get
ice cream on the woman's ear!
[HOTARO]
And there you have it.
Ah... So that explains why
it isn't there anymore.
[HOTARO] Either it washed off
while she was swimming
or she just wiped
it off herself.
Case closed. Mystery solved.
You know, Oreki...
Yeah, what's up?
[ERU]
Well, um... It's just...
That was great! I think
the way you're able
to figure things out makes
you a really special person!
Heh. Flattery will get
you nowhere with me.
--[SATOSHI] Hm.
--[MAYAKA] Hm.
Sure.
And here I was
starting to think
we'd never hear another
snappy retort from you!
Would that be so bad?
You wouldn't think.
But you were totally weirding us
out for a little while there.
[HOTARO]
Hmph.
[ERU laughs]
Ah! Sorry! I just realized
I haven't thanked you yet.
Thanks a lot. Sorry to bother
you with something like this.
I made a big fuss.
And it was all for nothing.
Hey. I...
No, you shouldn't apologize.
I mean, I'm the one
who thought it was an
earring in the first place.
I'm sorry. Really.
Seriously, it's no big deal.
Alllriiight! I don't know
about the rest of you,
but all this searching
has made me hungry.
I could really go
for some ice crea--
What's up? Why'd you cut off
like that? Ah! Hyouka !
I seem to remember you solemnly
swearing to me that you
would have your Hyouka draft
done by tomorrow, rain or shine!
Well, Fuku.
Have you finished it yet?
Well, I guess you could say I
have it more or less finished.
Give or take a page or two.
So the answer is no. It isn't
finished. Is that correct?
Yeah. I guess you
could say that, too.
That is exactly
what I would say!
We're leaving! I'm taking
you home right now,
and you're going
to write that draft!
I don't care how long it takes,
I'm not letting you
out of my sight
until it's done!
Look. There's not
much left to do.
I can take care of it myself,
I promise, okay?
[MAYAKA]
I don't believe you!
Sorry to leave
like this, you guys,
but a deadline's a deadline.
See you tomorrow.
Well, wish me luck--ah! Ah!
[ERU chuckles]
I hope it doesn't take too
long to get the draft done.
Oh, I'm sure it will.
For those two, I think the
thrill is all in the chase.
I wish they'd get to it already.
The thrill is in the chase, huh?
Well, I guess I dragged
you along on a chase
of my very own, didn't I?
Sorry I'm always doing that.
Yeah, seriously.
You can be a real nuisance.
Hey, that's not a
nice thing to say.
On the other hand, maybe
that's not such a bad thing.
Huh?
Nothing. Just forget about it.
[ERU]
Oh.
That's right,
I was wondering...
With that woman...
What gave you the idea that
it was ice cream on her ear?
Oh, that's simple.
Just look around.
Ice cream's the only thing
in this place that's white.
[HOTARO] I guess there
is one other thing.
[ERU]
Huh?
Well. I should probably
get going now, too.
Have fun. I guess
I'll see you later.
Uh. Yeah.
[LIFEGUARD]
Hey!
Break time's over.
All right.
Man, what a pain.