[beeping]
[keyboard tapping]
[SATOSHI] Wow. Looks like
Sho made the finals.
[HOTARO]
Yeah. That's what it says.
[SATOSHI]
Mm-hm!
He's amazing.
Seeing something like
that makes me wonder
if I have any natural
talents, but I doubt it.
I'm pretty sure the gifted
genes skipped right over me.
I keep trying to
tell myself I'm just
a late bloomer. That's only
wishful thinking, though.
Come on, what do ya mean?
You're a human database.
[SATOSHI] Yeah, I am quite
proud of that trait:
my ability to store information.
But even if I put effort
into developing it,
I'll never be a quiz show king.
Really?
Heck no. And I resent it.
I envy people like Sho.
Being a talented genius has
its disadvantages, too.
Yeah, like what?
Extraordinary people don't
even have the option
to lead a normal,
boring existence
like the rest of us do.
Uh--
Hold on.
You think a mundane life
is better somehow?
You would think that.
You're such a weirdo.
[HOTARO]
Mm...
I wonder if you'll
actually be able
to live a normal life.
What is that supposed to mean?
[sighs]
Look, I've accepted
that I don't have
any special talents.
I think the jury is
still out on you, though,
so I'm gonna hold off on making
a determination a bit longer.
If you think I could live
an extraordinary life,
I have to question your
powers of observation.
Hey, I'm still
gathering evidence.
Gimme a break here.
Anyway...
We should probably hurry
along to the meeting.
Mayaka will have both our hides
if we show up late again.
[HOTARO]
That's for sure.
[HOTARO] It's summer vacation,
for crying out loud.
You're late!
Ah--!
[laughs nervously]
[MAYAKA]
Yeah, laugh it up.
You two are in deep trouble.
Where's Chitanda?
Oh. She hasn't
shown up yet either.
I'm a little worried.
That's a pretty stark disparity.
There's a disparity
in your behavior.
[ERU]
I'm so sorry I'm late!
There's a film screening!
You guys!
Do you wanna see a student film?
Class 2-F produced a movie,
and they're gonna
be showing it in a few minutes!
[SATOSHI]
Hm?
[ERU] I have a friend
who's in that class,
and we were just
talking about it.
That's actually why I was late.
She wants some outside
input on the film,
so she asked if
we would watch it.
[MAYAKA]
What kind of movie is it?
[ERU] Um, she said it
was a murder mystery.
[MAYAKA]
Oh, yeah?
[SATOSHI]
Well, that's right up our alley.
[ERU]
I think this is the place.
[ERU] We decided to take
you up on your invitation.
[IRISU]
Well, I'm happy to hear that.
Thanks for coming.
I appreciate you taking the time
to help us out with this.
This is Mayaka Ibara.
That's Satoshi Fukube.
And he's Hotaro Oreki.
We're all in the
Classic Lit Club together,
as I mentioned earlier.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Fuyumi Irisu.
Oh! Now I remember.
You and I have met before.
I thought you looked
familiar. I was right!
[IRISU]
Uh, I don't remember you.
Sorry about that.
Oh, we were both on
the cultural festival
planning committee.
We mediated that dispute
between the Light Music Club
and the Drama Club?
Talk about drama!
[HOTARO] I've never seen
Satoshi so eager to please.
Yeah, sorry, still
doesn't ring a bell.
[SATOSHI]
U-Uh-- No worries.
Hey, Chi, how do
you know this girl?
My family and the
Irisu family have been
close for generations.
I've know her for as
long as I can remember.
[HOTARO] Being old money sure
seems like a lot of work.
[IRISU] Anyway...
Here is a copy of the movie
the other kids in
my class produced.
I'd be grateful if
you would watch it
and tell me your
honest opinions of it.
Sure, we can't wait!
[HOTARO]
So all we have to do is watch it
and tell you what we think?
[IRISU]
Yes, is that strange to you?
[HOTARO] Well, if we don't
like it, does that mean
you're going to reshoot
the parts we criticize,
or are you just showing us
for some free publicity?
Neither.
Then I don't understand
what you gain
from showing it to us.
You bring up a legitimate point.
The purpose involves
your opinions,
but it's not about
the quality, per se.
I just think it's more
efficient to show you the film
before explaining further.
So?
I guess I'll wait and see.
[IRISU] Our movie doesn't
have an official title yet,
but the working
title is "Mystery."
Once the film is over,
I'll be asking you
specific questions,
so please pay attention.
All right. Let's get
things started.
I'll be back in a bit.
Happy hunting.
[HOTARO]
"Hunting?"
[NARRATOR 8A]
These students from Class 2-F
have decided to participate
in the Kanyasai.
They need supplies
from the Narakubo area
for their exhibit and are
now heading to the site.
How much farther is it?
Not much farther.
We should be there
in five more minutes.
You said the same thing
five minutes ago!
This is pretty tough going.
I'm hot, and I'm
starting to feel
tired and hungry.
You're not the only one
who is hot and tired!
Now! We gotta keep marching!
[MAYAKA sighs]
[HOTARO] About what I'd
expect from a student film.
[SUGIMURA]
Mm-hm. Yes, I see it.
That's Narakubo over there.
[KONOSU]
So awesome.
[KATSUTA]
You're right.
I think it was worth
the trek to get supplies.
All that aside, it would
be wise to find a place
to camp for the night before
hunting for materials!
[KONOSU]
You're right.
That looks like a good place,
over there, doesn't it?
Let's go see!
[KONOSU]
I dunno, guys.
I have a bad feeling about this.
A haunted theater!
A haunted theater?
It's so dusty.
The roof seems like it's
holding up okay, though.
It's too dangerous
to sleep in this room.
There's glass scattered about!
We need to find
somewhere to camp
before it gets dark out.
I think I found a
floorplan over here.
[SATOSHI]
Oh! It is a floorplan!
Let's split up and
explore the building!
Hey! That sounds dangerous!
And I am certain all the
doors in here are locked!
There has to be a set
of keys lying around
this place somewhere.
[SUGIMURA]
What is that? An office?
[SUGIMURA] What do you
think those keys are for?
[KONOSU] I think those
are the master keys.
We should leave them here.
It would be bad
if they got lost.
[SUGIMURA]
Yeah, that's a good idea.
[KONOSU] We found keys.
They should unlock
all the rooms in the house.
[KAITO] Okay, let's split up
and see what we can find.
[KONOSU]
Right.
If this were reality,
there's no way they'd all
split up, you know what I mean?
What are you getting at?
Something's about to happen.
I can feel it--can't you?
[MAYAKA growls]
[HOTARO]
What?
He was the one talking to me!
[NARRATOR 8A] The incident
occurred soon after.
[SATOSHI]
See, I told you so!
[MAYAKA growls]
[HOTARO]
Hm?
Did you find anything?
There are pieces of
broken mirror everywhere.
We can't use any of
the rooms I've seen.
None of the rooms that
I saw would work, either.
Hey, Sugimura!
What did you find up there?
[SUGIMURA]
Well, it's pretty clean, mostly.
The rooms in this wing...
...might be our best options.
Hey, where's Kaito?
He must still be lookin' around.
Let's go find him.
Maybe he found
something worth seeing.
Is this a sitting room?
[KATSUTA]
No Kaito here.
Hm? Not in here, either.
Farther down, maybe?
[KATSUTA]
This one's locked.
It won't budge.
That's kinda weird.
[SENOUE]
What should we do?
[KONOSU]
I'll go get the master keys.
[SENOUE]
Yeah, I'll come with you.
[SUGIMURA]
Kaito!
Th-There's blood everywhere!
[fake screams]
[YAMANISHI]
Oh, no. What is that?
[SENOUE]
[ERU gasps]
[HOTARO] I'm amazed she can
buy into this nonsense.
Damn it! He's dead!
[KATSUTA grunting]
[KATSUTA pants]
[KATSUTA]
Oh, no.
[MAYAKA]
Um... Is that it?
But, wait.
There's no way
that's the ending!
[IRISU]
That's all we have so far.
So, what's the point
of this screening?
I'd like to know
who you all think
is the culprit in the film.
[IRISU] I will explain the
whole thing in a moment,
but first, I want to hear
each of your opinions.
Technically speaking,
what would be your
impressions of our film?
Well, if I could
be perfectly honest,
I think it's a bit clumsy.
I agree with that assessment.
No matter how much passion
goes into a film,
without real skill,
it feels amateur.
But isn't that okay?
I mean it is an amateur film.
Yes. I think it's fine
enough work for what it is.
A student film should
get some leeway
to be a bit
self-indulgent, right?
[HOTARO]
Mm-hm.
[IRISU] Let's not get bogged
down discussing aesthetics.
I was just curious.
What's the most obvious
issue with the project,
as it stands?
The fact that it's
nowhere near finished?
Yes.
Even if it's not perfect,
we have to complete it.
The crew shot at
a unique location,
and we were only able to do
so during the summer break,
which has proven
to be problematic.
Why do you say that?
Did the shoot not
go as scheduled?
The actual shoot
went according to plan.
We were supposed to
wrap everything up
right on time, next Sunday.
Okay, so what's
the problem, then?
The script's not done.
Mayu Hongo has written manga,
which is more experience
than anyone else in class,
so she agreed to write
the hour-long screen play.
That's a tall order!
She did pretty well
with it, overall.
But when she reached
the point that you saw
in the film, she got very
sick and couldn't finish.
[gasps]
Wait a minute.
Do you expect us to take over?
I could never ask
anything like that of you.
Now then, getting back
to my earlier question.
Who do you think
committed the murder?
Hongo got sick just
as we were getting
to the resolution.
I think that someone
who watched the film
up to this point should
be able to deduce who did it.
But are there really
going to be enough clues
to figure that out in a
screenplay by a novice writer?
I believe there should be.
Hongo immersed herself
and focused mostly
on Sherlock Holmes. She
followed the Ten Commandments,
Nine Propositions,
and the Twenty Rules.
Oh, yeah?
What, like from the Bible?
No, Knox's Ten Commandments.
Those, plus the Nine
Propositions and Twenty Rules
dictate what makes
a good detective story.
Correct.
They say the keys to
solving the crime must
always be presented
fairly to the reader.
So, with that in mind,
who do you think
is the culprit in this case?
[HOTARO] That's what she
meant by, "Happy hunting."
I'm not very good with
that kind of question.
I store information. I don't
know how to interpret it.
Me, either.
I don't pay much
attention to details.
Though, I suspect there's
someone here who does.
[HOTARO]
Hm?
Don't look at me.
[SATOSHI]
Why not?
This is right up
your alley, isn't it?
You are the star detective of
the Classic Lit Club, after all.
C'mon, why the sour face?
I wasn't watching
with that in mind.
In that case, let's ask her
to show us the movie again.
What? Give me a break!
There's no need to overthink it.
I just want an outside opinion.
Oh, is that right?
Well, then I think Yamanishi
is the murderer for sure.
[gasps] What makes
you say that?
'Cause I don't like
her crappy attitude.
Oreki! Don't play around!
Hey, Irisu, why don't
you try to figure out
who the murderer is?
I don't have any
experience with mysteries.
No?
Well, if that's the case,
then why'd you let the class
choose it as the genre
for your project?
I wasn't attached
to the film yet
when they were
making those decisions.
I got back from my family
vacation to Hokkaido,
and the film was already
in this sticky predicament.
I jumped in the day before
yesterday to sort it out.
If I'd been involved, I doubt
it would have moved forward.
One more question.
Why did you call on
the Classic Lit Club
to help you out with this issue?
[IRISU]
Well, first, I knew Chitanda
would have my back on this.
And secondly, I heard all
about the Hyouka business.
Huh?
I didn't think anyone
else knew about that.
[HOTARO]
Did Miss Itoigawa tell her?
When I agreed to
help my classmates
out of this mess, I remembered
what I'd heard about you.
I thought that perhaps I could
enlist you as my detectives
and solve the
problem even faster.
Well, don't expect us
to do all the work.
Not at all.
I sincerely apologize if
I gave you that impression.
Please forgive me.
So, that's the end of
this morning's screening.
Well, then. Thanks for coming.
[gasps]
Hey! Please, wait a minute!
What's going to
happen with the end
of the movie, then?
I don't know.
We'll do our best
with what we have.
But I am bracing
for the possibility
that we won't finish.
We can't let that happen.
I would be heartbroken
to know all their hard work
was done in vain!
I just don't think
I could bear it!
[HOTARO]
What's it to her?
Irisu should be upset.
Yeah.
It would be frustrating to
leave it unfinished like that!
I agree.
You all came together
as a team to get it done.
And also, Hongo worked
herself to the point
of illness for this project!
Why would she go
to such great lengths
just to give up halfway through?
I just... I have to know!
[SATOSHI chuckles]
Let's help them out,
Hotaro. Why not?
Got something better to do?
We must do this, Oreki.
Let's avenge Hongo's death
and solve this crime!
Hongo isn't dead. She's sick.
Ah! Oh, that's right.
We have to help them, Oreki!
[HOTARO sighs]
What happens if we
do decide to help,
but we can't figure out
who the murderer is either?
Are we supposed to
just bow down and beg
for forgiveness from Class 2-F?
I don't want that
kind of responsibility.
[IRISU]
I'll make you a deal.
How about you act as observers,
rather than detectives?
Observers?
Uh--
You'd listen to the opinions
of our class's
appointed detectives,
then offer your viewpoints,
and that'd be the extent of it.
Well?
[sighs]
That sounds okay. Deal.
[gasps]
Thanks so much. I appreciate it.
[SATOSHI]
Irisu's family is pretty famous.
That's the reason
right over there.
The Irisus have run
the general hospital
for decades now.
Oh, so she's the heiress
to a giant medical fortune.
Yeah, but that's not
the only reason Irisu,
herself, is well-known
around here.
People at school have
given her a nickname.
Do you know what they call her?
No idea.
"The Empress."
Why--does she rule people?
Ugh, she's not a dominatrix.
[HOTARO] I set it up,
you knocked it down.
I salute you.
What are you doing?
Well, she's pretty, but
that's not the whole reason.
I've heard she can get
anyone to do her bidding.
People are drawn to her,
and before they know it,
she's manipulated them
into being her pawns.
What? Well, that's
not creepy at all.
Maybe, but I have to say,
the Empress was generous
enough to grant us
an audience with her.
We might do well to adopt
our own symbols in her honor.
What do you mean?
Mayaka should be... "Justice."
It's between that
and "Judgement."
I don't get it.
Symbols from the Tarot deck.
[HOTARO]
Huh.
Well, Fuku, what would you be?
"The Fool," I think.
Nah, "The Magician" is better.
I think Chitanda
should be "The Fool."
[gasps] Yeah, you're right.
"The Fool" really does suit me,
now that you mention it.
Impulsiveness is definitely
one of my
shortcomings, after all.
I'm lost.
[HOTARO]
Yeah, same.
What about Oreki?
That's a no-brainer.
He'd be "Strength."
Huh? Seriously?
If I had to pick, I would
label him "The Star," instead.
Nope. This guy's
Strength, for sure.
It's perfect for him.
[HOTARO]
Hmph. I have a suspicion
that's not a compliment.
That's a fair assessment.
[HOTARO]
You're a total jerk.
Not a chance.
[doorbell rings]
[HOTARO]
Yeah?
Well, good morning, Oreki.
I thought we could
walk together.
[HOTARO grumbles]
[HOTARO] Does she have to be
so polite all the time?
Good morning, everyone!
[MAYAKA]
Morning.
[SATOSHI]
Mornin'!
I'm excited that we get
to meet the detectives today.
I'm looking forward to
listening to their hypotheses
about the murderer.
When did you have time
to make this happen?
Over chat.
Kamiyama High School has
a private online chat room
that only the students
are allowed to use.
Wow! I didn't know that!
You'll have to show me!
Yeah, that sounds fun!
[knocking]
[ERU]
Yes? Come on in!
Is this the
Classic Lit Club room?
It is.
Are you the girl who
Irisu sent from Class 2-F?
That's right. My name is Eba.
It's very nice to meet you all.
I believe I'm
supposed to take you
to meet our detectives?
Irisu told me she had briefed
you on the film situation.
All right, follow me.
[MAYAKA]
Chi, did you bring snacks today?
[ERU]
Yep!
I brought these fancy chocolates
someone sent to our house.
I thought that it would
be nice to share them
with everyone while
we were working today!
Sounds great!
I mean, after all, it's so
much harder to think clearly
when you're hungry, ya know?
Man, I can't wait to hear
the detectives' theories
about the film!
Aren't you so excited, Hotaro?
I'm glad you're all
having such a good time.
Hey, Eba! I have
a question for ya.
[EBA]
Go ahead.
[SATOSHI] Who are these
detectives, anyway?
[EBA] The assistant director,
the props master,
and the PR girl.
Cool!
So what exactly
is your involvement
in the filmmaking process?
I don't have anything to do
with it, as a matter of fact.
To be honest,
I wasn't interested.
[HOTARO]
Well how about that?
A girl after my own heart.
Eba, if you don't
mind my asking,
were you and Hongo close?
[EBA]
Why do you ask?
Oh.
I was just curious
about the kind of person
who would be able to write
a murder mystery
script like this.
[EBA]
If I had to describe her,
I'd say...
She's a no-nonsense, meticulous
person, really responsible,
kind to a fault, and fragile.
[EBA]
She's one of my best friends.
Interesting.
[EBA]
Here we are.
The film is on hiatus right now,
so I doubt anyone else
is gonna show up.
You shouldn't be interrupted.
[EBA] Everyone, I'd like you
to meet our detectives.
[HOTARO]
Next time:
"The Case of the Furuoka
Deserted Village Murder."