[GLENN] "'What are you?'
the demon asked.
'What drives you
to such lengths?
I can't fathom why you'd
risk and endure so much.'
Without hesitation,
the mage answered,
'That's simple, Demon Lord.
There are things
I wish to protect.'"
"It is this conviction and
understanding of my duties
that causes infinite power
to spring from my depths.
And lets me rise again.
Now prepare yourself,
Demon Lord,
for I shall defeat you.
and in doing so,
all shall be protected."
[GLENN] "The Demon Lord
screamed as he perished
beneath the mighty crackle
of the mage's holy lightning.
Their long battle had
finally come to an end."
[GLENN] I wanted to
be a mage of justice.
[hawk calls]
[SISTINE]
This is the city of Fejite,
located in the southern
region of the Alzano Empire.
This community was
born and developed
alongside the Alzano
Imperial Magic Academy.
It's just another theory.
They'll never know the real--
[RUMIA gasps]
[MALE TOWNSPERSON 1B]
Ow!
[RUMIA]
Are you all right?
[TOWNSPERSON 1B]
Mmm...
[RUMIA]
May I tend to that?
[RUMIA] The angels'
blessings be with you.
[SISTINE] The reason the
Alzano Empire is known
as a magical power in the world
is the Alzano Imperial
Magic Academy,
established over 400 years
after the Empire's founding.
Oh!
Seems you academy students
live up to the tales.
I'm impressed.
Actually, sir,
using our magic outside
the academy walls
is forbidden.
So can we keep this a secret?
[TOWNSPERSON 1B]
My lips are sealed.
Thank you.
[SISTINE]
Rumia!
[RUMIA]
Well, good day to you, sir.
Good luck in your studies.
I'm rooting for you.
[RUMIA]
Thanks.
[SISTINE] The academy
boasts a proud history.
It's hailed as the most
prominent school of its kind--
a training ground where
students can learn
the most advanced magical arts.
The most famous
mages in the world
are graduates from this
legendary institution.
You know, Rumia,
I told you you could
go on without me.
[RUMIA]
How could I?
I'm just a freeloading nobody
with so much to repay.
I could never leave
"Lady Sistine" alone
on the streets.
[SISTINE gasps]
I don't know if that's
some kind of joke,
but it's not funny.
You're part of the family now,
so feel proud.
Sorry, Sisti. I'll try.
Yeah, you better!
[BOTH giggle]
[RUMIA]
It's pretty unusual, though.
You hardly ever forget anything.
Were you too busy
thinking about him?
[SISTINE]
Maybe.
Why did Professor Huey
suddenly quit like that?
[RUMIA]
Who knows.
But word is we have a new
substitute starting today.
[GLENN panting]
Yeah, I heard. Aw, man.
I just hope it's someone as
passionate as Professor Huey.
[GLENN yelling]
Hey!
Out of the way!
Move, you brats!
[SISTINE, RUMIA scream]
[SISTINE]
Pay heed, great wind!
[GLENN yelling]
[RUMIA, SISTINE]
Huh?
[GLENN yelling]
Think that was a little much?
Yeah, probably.
I just panicked.
What do we do now?
That was unexpected.
You ladies okay?
He's late.
[GLENN]
Are you hurt?
[SISTINE]
No.
But shouldn't we ask you that?
These crowded streets can
get pretty dangerous, girls.
You should watch
where you're walking.
[SISTINE] You were the one
charging like a madman!
Sisti, don't.
You hit him hard
with that magic.
Just be glad he's okay.
[RUMIA]
Go on. Apologize.
[SISTINE]
I'm sorry.
[RUMIA]
I'm sorry, too, sir.
We should have
been more careful.
[GLENN]
Ha!
[laughing]
Well, I'm glad you agree!
[SISTINE, RUMIA]
Uh...?
Now that we've established
it's not my fault
in any way possible,
and your reckless walking
was 100% to blame,
let's talk consequences.
Normally they'd be severe.
But I can make an exception if--
[GLENN]
Nice.
You definitely seem familiar.
Have you and I...?
[RUMIA]
Uh...?
Hey!
What is wrong with you, man?
[GLENN yelling]
That's some nerve touching
a lady without permission!
He's scum!
I'm telling you, he's scum!
Late on his very first day?
I knew he was a bad choice!
I don't care if it
is just temporary!
We never should have let
a man of unknown origins
instruct at this academy!
ou've made yourself
clear, Halley.
But he came highly recommended
by Professor Celica Arfonia.
[HALLEY growls]
[SISTINE]
What's going on?
This class period is more
than halfway over now!
Maybe something
happened to him.
[WENDY]
A student would be one thing.
But a teacher at this
academy not showing up
to his own lecture?
It's unheard of!
Well, maybe he's
some kind of a bigshot.
I think a big bastard's
more like it.
[SISTINE] I'm gonna lodge
a complaint on behalf
of the entire student body!
--[door opens]
--[STUDENTS gasp]
[GLENN]
Hello, kiddoes. Sorry I'm late.
Well, it's about time, sir!
Do you have any idea what it
means to be a teacher at this--
[GLENN]
I'm not that guy from earlier.
[SISTINE]
How else would you know?
[GLENN]
I'm just that strong a mage.
Give me a break.
[GLENN sighs]
I'm Glenn Radars,
your new substitute
teacher extraordinaire.
I'll be helping you all with
your studies for the next month.
Teaching is a noble profession,
blah blah blah,
you're welcome in advance.
Let's see, my special
skills and hobbies...
There's no time
for introductions!
Can you please just
start the class?
[GLENN sighs]
Okay, fine.
I'll teach you.
I guess that is my job.
[RICK]
Surely you can't complain
if a professor recommended him.
I can if he's lousy!
This says his magic capacity
and memory are average,
and he's equally "okay"
in all schools of magic.
It seems his mage classification
is only Trede rank.
What?!
You're letting a run-of-the-mill
Trede teach here?!
At this academy, Quatrede
is the very minimum,
and we even have Quinde
and Sede orders on staff!
Hold on...
Are you sure he even
knows how to instruct
students of this caliber?
Or will he declare
self-study and sip tea?
[GLENN] Okay. Today's class
will be self-study period.
'Cause I'm tired.
--[STUDENTS chattering]
--[GLENN snoring]
[SISTINE]
Unacceptable!
[GLENN yells]
Oh, and did I mention he doesn't
have a teaching license?
[HALLEY gasps]
Still...
He does come recommended
by a professor,
so he can't be that bad.
I'm not hearing this!
I mean, he must have talent.
He was admitted to our
school at age eleven.
But on the other hand,
this says he left the
academy when he was only 15.
And went where?
I have no idea. The next
four years are unknown.
Obviously, that means he
just wasted all that time
doing nothing!
You see?
This boy is clearly a foolish
mage who can't be trusted!
I'm not so sure about that.
Headmaster, please!
Don't count on that witch
for something this crucial!
[CELICA]
A witch, huh?
That's not very polite.
[HALLEY gasps]
Oh, hello, Celica.
When did you get here?!
[CELICA] That'd be helpful
to know, wouldn't it?
But let's focus on
what matters most.
[HALLEY yells]
[CELICA] You can call me names
all day long if you desire.
I don't really care.
But I will not tolerate
you speaking ill of him.
Take it back.
[HALLEY yelling]
Sorry, professor!
[CELICA]
Well...
I finally managed
to get him into class.
[RICK]
Is that right?
[CELICA] I want you to know
I truly am sorry about this.
[RICK sighs] We've thrust a
young mage with no achievements
to speak of into a teaching
role at one of our
most hallowed academies.
Halley's reaction
is only natural.
[CELICA]
I'll take full responsibility.
If he fails to perform
in this job,
you can consider
it my failure as well.
[RICK]
You'd really go that far?
Stake your reputation on him?
May I ask what he means to you?
[CELICA chuckles]
You may.
But you'll be disappointed.
There is no special connection.
Not really.
It's rather simple.
I just want him
to live a full life.
It still hurts.
[STUDENTS] I've never seen
anyone so lifeless before.
[GLENN sighs]
His handwriting's too sloppy.
Sistine whacked him hard
with her iron fist of rage,
but it still doesn't seem like
he's taking this seriously.
[SISTINE growls]
[GLENN] So then you do that,
and then, other stuff.
This guy is incoherent.
I can sort of follow.
[STUDENTS]
His eyes look dead inside.
Excuse me. I have a question.
Sure, why not.
Um, it's about the runic spells
you introduced in the last
section, Professor Radars.
I'm not seeing a
translation for them
into our standard language.
[GLENN sighs]
[GLENN]
Uh... Let's see.
Translation, translation.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I don't either!
That sucks.
Just look it up yourself, okay?
All right, that does it!
You think that's an
appropriate response
to Lynn's perfectly
good question?
I don't know!
Should I make something up?
Would that be better?
If a teacher can't answer
a student's question,
it's his job to look it up
and have it ready for
the following class.
That's education 101!
Okay.
But if she looks it up herself
she won't have to wait,
now, will she?
Wait time is not the issue!
Easy, Sisti.
Oh, now I get it.
Do you guys not know how
to use a runic dictionary?
Is that the deal?
Because it's really
not so--[bell ringing]
That's it for this period.
Later, nerds!
Wait, you haven't
even given us our--
Told you he was a bastard.
What's with that
so-called teacher?
He's so unmotivated!
Now, now.
[SISTINE] And he's supervising
our next alchemy lab, too,
isn't he?
[RUMIA]
Think so.
[SISTINE] I swear,
he's gonna give me ulcers.
You gonna be okay, Sisti?
I don't know.
I think I need some healing.
Huh? Whoa!
[RUMIA gasps]
[sighs] Nothing like a
little snuggling with you
to make me feel better.
Your skin's so silky
smooth and pretty.
Oh, knock it off, Sisti.
Come on!
Hey!
Sisti, please!
You're embarrassing me!
Wow. You just
keep on developing.
These are impressive.
Am I not getting the same
nutrients into mine, or what?
No fair!
This isn't healing me at all.
It's just making me jealous!
[GLENN]
Waiting is such a pain!
Come on!
Why do you girls have to change
for an alchemy lab anyway?
[RUMIA gasps]
[SISTINE]
Get out!
No! I won't!
At least not yet!
First I must speak about this
super-cliché turn of events!
Why should a man panic
and avert his eyes?
Are we not all just
fellow humans?
Getting my face smashed
in merely for glimpsing
semi-nude women that
are right in front of me
is hardly a just trade!
Would that not
make me the victim?
[GIRLS growl]
[GLENN]
So I'll make it count.
And burn this image
into my brain!
[yells]
I can't believe it.
How could he cancel
the whole alchemy lab?
I'm here to actually
learn and get better!
[RUMIA] I understand
how you feel, Sisti,
I really do.
But let's enjoy lunch, okay?
I'm sorry.
It's just...
Your promise to your
grandfather, right?
If I'm ever gonna
solve the mystery
of Melgalius's Sky Castle,
there's so much more about
magic I need to learn.
Every day I don't improve
feels like a lost opportunity.
[GLENN]
Hey, girls.
Ah, that's nice.
Oh, come on!
So good.
Professor Radars,
you're attacking that food
with some real passion.
So I guess you like to eat, huh?
Sure.
Food's one of my few pleasures,
especially when I
don't have to cook!
[laughs]
Wow.
Today's stir-fry does
look pretty tasty.
[GLENN]
You're not wrong.
These kilua beans are
in season right now.
Oh, I didn't know.
I'll have to try some
at our next meal.
[GLENN]
Why wait? Try mine.
'Kay.
If you don't mind.
Mmm! So much flavor!
[GLENN]
I know, right?
And what about you, punchy?
You sure that's enough food?
It's hardly a substitute
professor's place
to tell me what I should
and should not be eating.
[GLENN] Gotta eat to grow.
Just sayin'.
It's none of your business!
But the truth is I eat
light so I won't be sleepy
during my afternoon classes.
Though of course,
you're going to be
teaching them today,
so I guess it wouldn't
matter if I went
into a full food coma.
That's a roundabout way to talk.
If there's something
on your mind,
why don't you
come out and say it?
Okay, Mr. Sub.
I'll tell you exactly
what I think.
First of all--
It's okay. I know
what you were thinking.
You wanted to try it, too.
Naughty glutton.
I did not, you jerk!
I was going to say--
But you should share too.
[SISTINE] What are you doing?
That's mine!
Stop ruining my life!
Sisti...
How can you call
yourself a teacher?
Well...
It's only temporary.
[GLENN] You want me to sub
at the magic academy?
[CELICA] Just till we
find a real professor.
Would you do it?
Sorry, no way.
No way?
Why not, Glenn?
[GLENN]
It's a bad idea.
I'm not qualified to
teach magic to a carpet.
Well, it's true.
You don't have a
teacher's license, but...
I'm busy working this
whole cool image thing
and you're killing it
with real world
sub teacher crap?
Did I fail to mention
you're not allowed to refuse?
Oh? What if I do?
Then I'll have to
strike you with lightning.
Or would you prefer
to be burned in a fire?
Or frozen in ice?
That could be fun.
[chuckles]
[GLENN] Please keep supporting
me! I don't wanna have a job!
Return to the
cycle of providence,
five elements to elements,
and sever the links
between images and truths!
[CELICA]
Next time I won't miss!
[GLENN screams]
[GLENN]
Well, on to afternoon classes.
[KASH]
Again?
Okay, next class.
[GEEVIL]
Even his writing's lazy.
[GLENN]
And the third.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[SISTINE] I really, really
didn't wanna say this...
[GLENN]
Then please don't.
I belong to the noble
Fibel family of mages.
A family with significant
influence on this academy,
and if I tell my father
how you're behaving
in this classroom,
I could easily have you fired!
What? Whoa, really?
I don't wanna resort to
that kind of intervention.
But unless you
clean up your act,
I'm afraid I'll have no choice!
Please tell your father
I'm counting on his complaint.
[SISTINE gasps]
Aw, man, what a huge relief!
I can't quit, but if I'm
fired it's out of my hands!
I never wanted
to work here anyway.
I knew this would be a disaster!
[RUMIA]
Sisti, don't!
[GLENN]
Huh?
Ouch.
She just challenged
him to a magic duel?!
Well this day just got better.
You accept?
Or are you scared you can't win?
A duel?
That a joke?
Am I smiling, punk?
[STUDENTS chattering]
You can't do this, Sisti!
Quick! Apologize!
It's not too late!
Just pick up your glove!
What is it you want from me?
[SISTINE] If I win, you have to
correct your terrible attitude
and actually teach.
[GLENN]
You do understand if I win,
you'll have to accept my demand
no matter what it might be?
I know how duels work.
[GLENN]
You sure you wanna risk it?
Jeez.
What's he going to demand?
He makes it sound like
it's something awful.
[SISTINE] This education
is everything to me.
I can't just sit and
watch someone like you
sleep at the front of class
and make a mockery
of out of our academy
and what I've dedicated
my life to learn!
You have no respect for magic!
[sighs]
Unbelievable.
I didn't even think
there was anyone left
who still lived by those
silly old customs
let alone some teenage girl.
But okay.
If that's what you want,
then let's do it.
[RUMIA]
Huh?
He accepted it?
That's crazy!
A duel between a
professor and a student?
I've never heard of that before!
This is so fun it feels wrong.
[GLENN]
Here's the deal.
Though I think a brat like you
could use some punishment,
I don't want to injure you.
So the only spell
we'll use in this battle
will be Shock Bolt, and all
others will be prohibited.
You accept?
[SISTINE] The challenged
mage reserves the right
to decide the rules of the duel.
So I have no argument.
Who do you think
is gonna win this?
I have to go with the professor.
Though he's gonna
be in real trouble
if he underestimates Sistine.
It's weird he picked Shock Bolt.
Well, he said he wants
to go easy on her.
Not sure that's it.
[WENDY]
What do you mean?
It's true that Shock Bolt
is relatively simple magic.
It's one of the first
spells we learn to cast.
A defensive move
summoning electricity
to paralyze your opponent.
The chant is only three lines.
"Thunder sprites, pay heed,
and strike with
your electric shock."
Straightforward, right?
But in actual combat,
the winner's always the mage
with enough mastery of the spell
to condense it into one line
and be the first to cast.
He's confident he can
cast quicker than she can?
Guess so.
[WENDY] I heard Professor
Arfonia backed him.
He must be strong.
Don't look so tense.
I'm sure you're nervous,
but I'm not here to hurt you.
If you wanna practice on me,
you can take the first shot.
[SISTINE]
Come on.
I am Sistine Fibel.
As long as I accept
the mantle of that name,
I can't allow this man
to carry on with impunity!
Even if he is the more
powerful spell-caster,
even if I'm forced to eat dirt,
I can't back down!
That's my pride as a mage!
Here I go!
Thunder sprites, shock!
[GLENN screaming]
[STUDENTS gasp]
Right in the face.
What happened?
Did I misunderstand the rules?
[GLENN]
Wow, you're not bad.
Whatever. I'll give you
the first round.
It's fine since we're
playing best of three!
[SISTINE]
Are we?
Okay, here I go!
It's time for round two!
Thunder sprites,
take heed, and--
[SISTINE]
Thunder sprites, shock!
[GLENN screams]
Ah, that was rough.
You're way more
decent than I expected.
Guess I've been goofing
off too much early.
You know, since
it's best of five.
Five?
But you just said it
was best of three!
Well, fine. Here goes!
Whoa! What is that thing?
Heh! I can't believe
you fell for that! Thunder--
[SISTINE]
Thunder sprites, shock.
[GLENN screams]
Wait a second,
Professor Radars.
Can you not cast Shock Bolt
with a single chanting phrase?
What are you
talking about, punchy?
Shortening a chant is heresy
and a grave insult to magic!
I say that because I'm a man of
principle, not 'cause I can't!
[STUDENTS]
He totally can't.
I'm not even gonna touch that,
but I've obviously
won this duel!
So as I demanded,
starting tomorrow
you're going to teach us--
I'm sorry.
Did I agree to that?
That doesn't ring a bell.
You must be confused.
But more importantly,
your spell-casting
isn't half bad!
And since it's my first day,
I'll cut you some slack
and say you were so close
it was almost a draw!
[laughing]
So, now what?
But it won't be close next time!
See ya!
[yelps]
[SISTINE]
This guy is hopeless.