[ZELOS] The Alzano
Imperial Magic Academy?
Didn't they just suffer a
violent attack the other day?
Why would she go there now?
You are aware,
Commander Zelos, aren't you?
The woman at the center
of the incident was
our own Princess Ermiana.
So then Her Majesty is concerned
about the Princess's safety?
[ALICIA'S MAID 4A] Queen Alicia,
I've brought the grand commander
of the imperial guard,
Mr. Zelos, to see you.
I'm here regarding
your impending visit
to Alzano Imperial
Magic Academy.
Yes.
Well, ma'am, I shall do
all I can to keep you safe
throughout your travels
and the competition itself.
I appreciate that.
If I may beg your pardon,
at the school is--
[ALICIA] Is the girl we
declared to be dead.
[ZELOS]
Yes, ma'am.
As of now, very few
individuals within the Empire
are aware of that fact.
However, if this visit were
to somehow bring it to light...
[ALICIA]
Zelos.
I apologize for overstepping
my bounds, ma'am.
Thank you.
I shall keep your
advice in mind.
Ma'am.
[ALICIA]
It's been three years now.
And I...
I imagine that girl must
hate me for what I did to her.
Still, even if she hates me,
even if she can
never forgive me,
so long as she's
alive and healthy...
That's all I
could ever hope for.
[SISTINE] So who wants to
compete in the flying race?
How about the
transmutation event?
[SISTINE sighs]
This is bad.
You guys,
the competition is next week.
Hey, let's all just try
to do our best, okay?
No way.
If we enter,
we're just gonna lose.
Well, winning isn't
the only reason to enter,
you know.
Eh, I'll pass, guys.
I just don't really feel
like competing right now.
Yes, but this is
a rare opportunity.
[SISTINE] And some of you
didn't participate last year.
Please, there's no need
for us to go out of our way
to humiliate ourselves
when the queen herself
will be there watching.
This is what happens
when you try too hard
to be nice and include everyone.
Oh, c'mon!
Are you serious here?!
Of course.
[GLENN] Just leave everything
to me, Glenn Radars,
the greatest teacher
who ever teached!
Oh, great, here we go.
[GLENN]
What's the problem?
Still having trouble filling
out the event rosters?
Here, give me the list,
white cat.
[SISTINE sighs]
I told you to stop calling me
that demeaning nickname.
I'll use my
ultra-intuitive judgment
as your super
charismatic instructor
to put the squad together.
And I'll make sure
that you guys win!
No messing around.
We will win!
[chuckles]
[GLENN] All right. The duels
with their higher point values
go to...
White cat, Gibul, and Kash.
We'll entrust Wendy
with speed deciphering.
Rodde and Ky can
take the flying race.
Let's give magic
sniping to Cecil,
and long-range
weightlifting to Teresa.
Of course,
Rumia's the only choice
for mental defense.
We'll have Lynn handle
transmutation. And then...
[RUMIA] Professor Radars is
making sure we all have a spot!
Okay, that about settles it.
No way! This is so not cool!
How can you just
pull me out of the
dueling competition like that?
[GLENN] While your repertoire
of spells is incredible,
you can be a little slow
and clumsy sometimes.
[WENDY gasps]
Them's the brakes, champ.
That's why we're
going with Kash,
who has great
judgment and reflexes.
But you, Wendy,
are a cut above the rest when
it comes to Read Language,
so I think you can
run up the score
in speed deciphering.
Well, if that's
the case, then fine.
The flying race relies
on gravity manipulation
black magic.
Which Rodde and Ky
oughta be able to handle.
Teresa, you may not
realize it yet yourself,
but you have an affinity for
long-range manipulation spells.
Alf, Bix, Cycer.
Granzia is more about
teamwork than skill.
Since you three
are always together,
I figure you're the best suited.
Plus you're all pretty
good at synchronization.
[SISTINE]
I don't believe it.
He's actually been paying
close attention to us.
Professor Radars
may be a total slacker,
but I guess he has
another side to him, too.
Now then, anything else?
Awesome. We're all set!
[GLENN]
Hell yeah!
I'm killing this teacher thing!
[GLENN]
I'm broke! I'll starve!
You gotta give me an advance
or an allowance or something!
[RICK]
Sorry, son,
but you know we can't
pay you in advance.
You reap what you sow!
So take care of this
problem on your own!
[GLENN] Jeez, do you
hear this, Headmaster?
This is precisely what's
wrong with Celica!
[CELICA] Oh, yeah?
And how exactly am I the one
to blame for this, huh?
Hey! You'll crush my skull!
Save me, Mama!
Well, now,
there is a special bonus
you could potentially earn.
Special bonus?
That's right.
The instructor who's
responsible for the class
that wins the magic competition
traditionally receives
some financial compensation.
You know, an incentive
to reward good teaching.
Oh, yeah, that's it!
[GIBUL]
Professor, could you just stop?
Huh? You know a better
way to organize the team
so that we can win?
Then let's hear it.
[GIBUL] Yeah, it's simple,
Professor Obvious.
Use only the best students
and have 'em cover all events.
That's standard procedure.
It's what all the
classes do every year.
Huh?
[GLENN]
Seriously?
We can just use the good
students over and over again?
And that's totally okay?
[SISTINE]
No, Gibul!
What's the point of winning
if only a few
students participate?
Professor Radars promised he
would lead our class to victory.
And the best part is
he thinks the whole class
can do it together.
[GIBUL]
Okay, have fun losing.
Am I right, Professor?
Uh, yeah, sure.
You really nailed it.
Oh, I don't think they're
on the same page here.
[GLENN]
I'm screwed.
Figures all the other
classes would only
be sending the best of the best.
Now I remember
the magic competition.
I'd forgotten all about it
since I never entered.
[STUDENT 4A]
Child of flame, pay heed,
and light a fire
at my fingertips!
[GLENN]
Oh, well.
[KASH] You class one
clowns need to back off!
[KREISS] Well, you class
two losers are in our way!
Oh, yeah? Well, screw you!
Class one's supposed
to be practicing here now,
so beat it!
[KASH]
I'm gonna beat you--
All right, okay, just chill out.
[HALLEY]
Kreiss!
I told you to secure
a location for us!
Oh, hey, there!
If it isn't my old pal, Harlem.
Halley! Halley Astry!
Are you mocking me?
Uh, so, Hal-whatever-it-is,
is your class practicing
for the competition, too?
Naturally, and as long
as I'm leading them,
anything short of
victory is unthinkable.
Wow, that's awesome, Big Guy!
Good luck!
Okay, whatever.
Just clear the area.
Okay, we'll move
back by that tree.
That'll give you guys
enough room, right?
You don't get it.
I want everybody from class two
to get out of my sight
right this instant.
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--Come on, now,
that's just a little excessive,
don't you think?
Glenn Radars,
I hear that you intend
to have everyone in
your class participate.
[GLENN]
Yeah, that's right.
[HALLEY] A class that's
throwing the competition
by using its least capable
students is a nuisance,
and taking up space
in the practice area
that should be reserved
for serious teams!
[GLENN]
With all due respect,
this here is the best
possible lineup for our class.
And we've got our
sights set on serious victory,
so don't get yourself caught
off guard by underestimating us.
You talk a big game, but--
Care to make it interesting?
Huh?
[GLENN]
I'll bet three months' salary
on my class winning this thing.
What do ya say?
Will ya take the bet, Big Guy?
[GLENN]
Oh, crap!
I just blurted that out
'cause he was pissing me off!
[HALLEY] Magical research
requires vast sums of money.
Now, I don't intend to lose,
but on the off-chance...
All right.
I'm confident enough in my class
to wager on them, as well!
Three months' salary it is!
Ya got guts, Harry,
I'll give you that.
[GLENN]
Oh, man! Time to grovel!
Gotta put everything I have
into my unique magic,
the brown nose Jumping Grovel!
That's enough!
Professor Halley,
I don't see any
justification for your claim
to the practice field.
If you continue this
unsportsmanlike behavior,
I'll be forced to bring this up
with the Academy leadership.
Understood?
[HALLEY]
Damn noble-born brat.
Besides, Professor Radars
won't be intimidated.
[GLENN]
Huh?
We're going to fight fair
and square at the competition
with everything we've got
to earn the victory
the right way.
Am I right, Professor?
[GLENN]
Uh, yeah, sure.
[HALLEY]
Heed this!
I will make sure you regret
ever daring to oppose me!
Did you all hear
how much faith
Professor Radars has in us?
There's no way we can lose!
[STUDENTS cheering]
Let's win this, shall we?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GLENN]
No problem.
Yeah, I really don't think
they're on the same page.
[RUMIA] Hey, Professor Radars
is pretty cool, isn't he?
He's usually such an oaf.
He should try being serious
like this more often.
[RUMIA giggles]
You're not being
honest with yourself.
What are you talking about?
[RUMIA giggles]
[RUMIA crying]
Mother!
Don't leave me!
I'll be a good girl!
Please, please don't hate me!
[RUMIA gasps]
Hey, don't cry. Keep quiet.
[RUMIA]
I don't wanna die.
Help me! I don't wanna die!
Please!
It's all right.
I'm on your side, okay?
There's still some bad guys.
So you can be as frightened
of me as you want,
but if you'll just stop crying,
then I can try to save you.
[SISTINE]
Rumia?
Dinner's ready.
Oh, uh, thank you, Sisti.
Hey, what is that?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's nothing at all.
Anyway, tomorrow's the
big competition, right?
Even the queen herself
will be there,
so we all have to do our best.
[SISTINE]
Rumia, about tomorrow.
Um...
[RUMIA] Look, thanks a lot
for worrying about me,
but I already know
who my true parents are.
They're your parents, Sisti.
[RUMIA]
Now let's go.
Mother and Father
are waiting for us.
[MR. FIBEL]
Sorry, girls.
We had some last-minute
work come in for tomorrow.
We were really looking
forward to being there
to see you both have
your big moment, but...
[SISTINE]
We understand.
You guys can't help it
if you're both busy with work.
Yeah, please don't
worry about it.
Illyana!
My girls are so sweet
I'm gonna cry!
[gasps]
Are my daughters angels?
No, goddesses!
They must be--Agh!
Sorry, girls. It's work
we just can't get out of.
[MR. FIBEL choking]
Oh, yeah, we get it.
But next time, girls,
I promise you,
I'll find a way
to thre--[laughs]
I mean, request time off.
[RUMIA laughs]
That's not necessary.
[SISTINE, RUMIA sigh]
Now, now.
Hang in there, my dear.
You're in an awfully good mood.
That's because today,
I'll get to see her,
even if it's from afar.
Now, ma'am, about
that pendant there.
[ALICIA]
Of course.
Why don't you wear
this one instead?
[STADIUM cheering]
[ALICIA]
Ladies and gentlemen
in the name of Queen Alicia
the Seventh of Alzano,
let the annual magic
competition hereby commence.
[STADIUM cheering]
[HALLEY] Hmph! To think my
class will be the one to win
before the queen...
[stomach growls]
[GLENN] I can feel the applause
echo in my empty stomach.
[RUMIA]
Figures.
Now they're rounding
the final corner!
Here comes Ky with the baton
pass to Rodde, and Rodde...
There he goes,
third through the goal!
Class two is third
in the flying race!
What a shocking upset!
We did it!
Rodde and Ky
actually came in third!
[GLENN]
No way!
Professor, did you have
a trick up your sleeve?
Why, of course I did!
But really, it's just a matter
of some simple math equations.
Since this was a
long-distance race...
...pacing's more
important than speed.
So I just ran some
calculations to figure out
the magic power they'd expend.
We might really pull this off
if we just follow Profess--
Don't get so carried
away just 'cause
by some miracle
you came in third.
[KASH]
What did you say?!
Stop it, Kreiss.
Let them have
this one tiny moment.
[KREISS]
Yes, Professor.
This was Professor
Radars' strategy!
Long as we've got
him on our side,
we can't lose to class one!
Right, you guys?
[ALF]
Yeah, that's right!
[BIX]
We'll get you back!
[GLENN]
Hey, knock it off!
Quit raising the bar for me!
[CELICA laughing]
Well done, class two!
Is that appropriate, Professor?
Oh, my bad.
Sorry 'bout that, Queenie.
We're cool, right?
[ALICIA'S MAID 4A]
Miss Celica,
you're being
quite disrespectful.
[ALICIA]
It's all right.
She's an old friend.
The two of us go way back.
You seem to be
having fun, Celica.
Yeah, I am, Alice.
It's pretty refreshing,
actually.
Is this man truly
all that incredible?
[CELICA]
He's just an average guy,
but always manages to do
something unexpected.
He's been that way
forever, right?
Yes.
[STADIUM cheering]
Cecil from class two makes
the top four in magical sniping!
Yeah, I did it!
Just like Professor Radars said!
[ARS]
Class two!
A knight speaks only the truth,
guided by courage.
[ARS]
Correct!
Wendy from class two
crushes the competition
in speed deciphering!
[WENDY] Just like Professor
Radars thought I would!
[stomach growls]
[GLENN] These kids are
doing better than I expected!
At this rate, I might get
to hold onto my salary!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GLENN] You guys really are
giving it your all out there.
Shoot.
Make me feel like
trying harder, too.
What a pain.
Next up, mental defense!
Which means your
humble announcer, Ars,
will make his way down
to the field for a closer look.
[JAILL]
Hey. Girlie.
Some free advice for ya.
Drop out now.
Jaill from class five,
aren't you?
Well, you're so kind
to worry about me,
but everyone else
has been doing their best,
so I owe it to them
to try my hardest.
Besides, your class is in
second place now, right?
Yeah, so what?
Well, my class
is in third place.
So if I beat you here,
that means you won't be
in second place.
Hmph. That's interesting.
[SISTINE]
Rumia!
[GIBUL] Professor Radars,
you wouldn't by chance
be using her as
a sacrificial pawn
in mental defense,
now, would you?
[GLENN]
Huh?
[GIBUL] Rumia excels
at healing white magic,
but she's not as adept
with other kinds.
Using her as cannon fodder here
is certainly the logical move.
Hey, you take that back!
Professor Radars would never--
Sacrifice Rumia?
You mean you're not?
Of course I'm not.
She'll be all right.
You should know
better than anyone
that girl's got nerves of steel.
That's right!
[ARS] Now, to kick off the
mental defense competition,
please welcome this
Academy's magical professor,
an authority on mental
manipulation magic,
the Sede, Count Zest!
Salutations.
[STADIUM cheering]
Without further ado,
let's begin round one!
Count Zest, if you please!
[ZEST] I'll start with Sleep
Sound, to feel everyone out.
[SISTINE] Rumia, don't
push yourself too hard!
[ZEST] Rest to the body,
and let those eyelids fall.
[STUDENTS]
My guardian spirit, pay heed,
and protect my mind from evil!
He's down!
The sleepy dropout
hails from Class One!
But right now all eyes
are on last year's champion,
Jaill, who will be
tough to beat!
Though personally,
my attention's on the lone girl
Rumia of class two.
How 'bout you, Count?
Ah, indeed.
How much can such a
lovely young girl endure?
How deeply can I corrupt
her innocent little heart?
[laughing]
He's... a pervert!
We should fire his ass.
Next up, Confusion Mind!
[STUDENT 4F]
Oh, it burns!
[ARS]
Class eight is out!
I'm not into boys!
Why can't Rumia be stripping?
At least try to hide
your lechery, Count!
Back to it.
Next up is Charm Mind!
Uh-oh, those guys
are being manipulated
by the pervy count!
I told you,
I'm not into boys!
[ARS] That's the count's
high-speed chanting!
Creeper levels are
maxing out here, folks!
[STADIUM]
Ugh!
[ARS] That disgusting
display of dental dexterity
has eliminated most
of the contestants,
leaving only the defending
champion, Jaill,
and class two's Rumia!
Wow, I had no idea that
Rumia was this strong!
Mind Up is a spell
that can be used
to boost one's mental fortitude.
The stronger your nerves are,
the more effective it is.
Now see, Rumia's mindset--
hell, her mind itself isn't
like a normal person's.
It's kinda like she's
always prepared to die.
It's freaky.
Which is why I thought this'd
be an easy win for Rumia,
but that Jaill
is something else.
Oh, well.
[ZEST] Well, then, it would
seem the time has come
to move on to Mind Break.
[ARS]
Here it is, folks!
One of the most advanced
and dangerous spells!
Breaking the target's mind
and rendering them unconscious!
[ZEST]
Here I go!
Listen to the warble
of wicked birds,
thy will carried to the heavens,
thy mind rendered blank!
Are you two still all right?
Ha, this is nothing.
I'm fine. I've got this.
[ARS]
Incredible! They both survived!
How 'bout that.
Not bad for a girl.
[RUMIA giggles] This might
get pretty rough, huh?
[JAILL]
You could always just quit.
[RUMIA] Aw, you don't
have to worry about me.
I'll be fine. I can't quit.
And I can't afford
to lose, either.
Professor Radars promised
we would win this!
He made us all believe we
can come together as a team.
That sub everyone's
talking about?
Ridiculous.
[RUMIA]
He's taught us a lot, actually.
So...
I can't let my classmates down!
[JAILL]
That so?
[ZEST]
In order to settle this match,
I'll increase the power.
Are you two mentally
prepared for that?
Here we go!
[ARS] Oh! Just like that,
Rumia falls to her knees!
Do you wish to surrender?
No, no, I'm fine.
--I can--
--[GLENN] She forfeits.
Yeah, class two
is dropping out here.
[RUMIA]
Professor?
It's all right.
I can keep going.
[GLENN]
You hung in there like a champ.
But Professor!
No, that's enough now.
Rumia.
If it's painful,
you don't have to do this.
You did great, kid.
You were just up against
the wrong opponent.
I never anticipated
someone like him.
Sorry about that.
No. Don't be. I had fun.
And I really felt
like I was fighting
on behalf of the
whole class, too.
[GLENN]
Oh, yeah?
Hey, Jaill,
now that you've won
in mental defense again,
do you have any words?
[ZEST] It appears Jaill
is unconscious on his feet!
[ARS]
Uh...
Meaning what?
Victory belongs to Rumia.
Even if she withdrew,
she already cleared the
previous Mind Break beforehand.
[ARS]
Unbelievable!
The winner is
Rumia of class two!
Rumia!
Congratulations, you did it!
Thank you!
[ALICIA] She's been blessed
with good friends
and a good mentor.
I'm so very happy
that I was able to be here
to see her smiling like that.
You know, if you had
mentioned anything to me,
maybe I could've
worked something out.
No, it's fine.
I know that the fact
that I abandoned her
isn't going to change.
Still, I feel very
satisfied today.
Especially after seeing her.
Seeing my Rumia like this.
[CELICA]
Is that really enough?
Just seeing her from afar--
is that enough for you?
Please, ma'am.
Why don't you try being
honest with yourself,
if only for today?
That's right!
[chattering, laughing]