[ELEANOR]
Her Majesty's necklace.
The truth is it's been enchanted
with a conditional curse.
[CELICA gasps]
We're putting her to use.
The necklace will
make sure of that.
The Researchers of
Divine Wisdom's mission
will succeed no matter the cost.
[CELICA] What?
You're with the Researchers?
Under the conditions
of the curse,
there's only one
way to save her.
If the queen is
to live past sundown,
the blood ransom must be paid.
[CROWD cheering]
[ARS] And their strong
showing continues!
Despite class one's efforts,
Professor Radars'
class two refuses to yield!
[CELICA]
Come on, Glenn.
Rumia, you okay?
I'm fine.
I beseech creation.
Grant unto my hands--
a great blade.
That was alchemy, wasn't it?
So now the Court Mage
Corps is after us too?
Silver ice wolf!
Race forth, clad in blizzard!
[RE=L]
That won't work, Glenn.
You're done.
[GLENN]
Close combat with alchemy
and long-range sniping
magic at the same time?
I'm screwed!
[RE=L gasps]
[GLENN]
Uh...?
Long time no see, Glenn.
Uh...! No way! Albert?!
[GLENN] Are you insane?!
You nearly killed me!
[RE=L]
Glenn. That hurts.
How is cutting me
in half your Plan A?
[RUMIA]
Uh, Professor?
Who are these people?
[GLENN] They're comrades from
my old Imperial Army days.
They serve in the Court Mage
Corps Special Forces.
Albert there is Executioner
Number Seventeen. The Star.
And Re=L is Number Seven,
The Chariot.
I'd like to say they're
so trustworthy we can relax.
But then I'd be lying.
Hey. That was
too careless, Albert.
You can't cast
military-grade spells
on a city street.
[GLENN] You think pulling
swords out of the ground's
any better?!
This is no time
for horseplay, Glenn.
The Guard have
detained the queen.
And though they claim
it's for her own security,
it appears they're
acting on their own
to eliminate the
former princess.
[GLENN]
And Celica?
[ALBERT]
She's in the VIP seats,
but so far she's done nothing.
[GLENN] That's weird--
she could easily handle guards.
And she was talking
funny to me, too.
Man. What's going on here?
Why would the Imperial
Guard be going after Rumia?
And why now?
[ALBERT] Those are questions
we can't yet answer.
We can't think
our way through this.
Right now we need to act,
and lucky for you I have a plan.
Yeah? Let's hear it.
I'll start by charging the
enemy line from the front.
Then after that,
Glenn will charge the enemy line
from the front.
Then Albert will
be the third wave,
and charge the enemy line
from the front.
Ow! What'd I say?
How can you possibly think
that's a strategy, moron?!
You're like a battering
ram with a ponytail!
[RUMIA giggles]
I'm guessing you're
friends, Professor?
What? Are you kidding?
Whatever.
I'm just glad you guys
aren't making me fight you.
So, does that mean you'll help?
Depends what you need.
[GLENN] Celica wouldn't say
much, but she did tell me
to "present myself
to the queen."
I think the only way out
of this mess is to do just that.
How will that help?
[GLENN]
Beats me.
But we're talking
about Celica Arfonia.
Former Special
Forces Executioner
number Twenty-One.
The World, Septende rank
and the greatest mage
on the whole damn continent.
She's got a nasty temper,
and is petty as hell.
But when she talks,
you'd be a fool not to listen.
It's gonna be a gamble
no matter what we try.
I'd rather bet on her.
[ALBERT] Very well.
I'll trust you on this.
[ARS]
Class one absolutely dominates
Detection And Unlocking,
stopping class two's win streak
and taking back the lead!
I knew we were dead
without the professor here!
Where in the world is he?
How could he miss this?
[ALBERT]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're the students
from class two, correct?
I'm Albert Frazer
and I'm an old friend
of your professor, Glenn Radars.
This is Re=L.
I heard Glenn took a job
teaching at this school,
so I came to cheer him on today.
But something urgent
has just come up
that he must attend to,
I'm afraid.
[SISTINE]
Uh...
And so he sent me
with this message.
"Class, I'm leaving
Albert in charge.
I know it's a shock,
but you can deal.
Also..."
[ALBERT]
"...don't be idiots. Win this."
That's all.
Don't be idiots and win this?
That sounds like him,
but they're total strangers!
Trust us, Sisti.
How'd you...?
All right, fine.
If that's what he said,
then so be it.
You're in charge.
[WENDY, KASH]
Sistine!
You sure it's okay?
We don't know them.
Listen, it doesn't matter
who's officially in charge.
Our goal is the same.
Our whole class is doing this
together to beat class one!
I guess it is up to us.
That's right.
And imagine what'll happen
if we do lose now.
[GLENN] Aw, you guys
are helpless without me.
You're so pathetic
it's kinda cute!
Sorry I couldn't
be there to rescue
my clumsy little puppies!
Sounds right.
Yeah, he'd never let it go.
It'd be super annoying!
[GIBUL] I have a gift
for ignoring teachers,
but that'd be too much
even for me.
Okay, guys! Come on!
Let's win this!
[ARS] All right,
only a few more events to go,
and class two's momentum
has taken a major hit!
Transmutation is next,
and if they lose this,
the overall win
could be out of their grasp!
[HALLEY]
I can't believe it.
He really is a no-show?
Without Radars in charge,
that class is nothing
but a mindless mob.
Seta. Kick them
while they're down.
Sure. My pleasure.
[DRAGON (SETA) growls]
[ARS]
Astounding!
Seta has transformed
into a ferocious dragon!
Scoring a nine, nine,
ten, and nine,
for a total of 37 points!
Has he just run away with this?
No. How can I top that?
Oh, Mr. Frazer, sir.
[ALBERT] Looks like you've
been putting a lot of work
into your image training.
So you should relax now.
And have fun
at this competition.
That's the point.
And besides, if anybody
tries to blame you
for our class losing,
then I'll give them
a big helping
of my iron fist.
[LYNN] That's exactly what
the professor said to me.
Good?
Yeah.
Next, we've got Lynn,
representing class two!
What transformation
is she going to attempt?
Now behold, phantasmagoria.
Enacted by myself.
This is for you, Professor!
[CROWD cheering]
[ARS]
An angel!
No doubt about it,
that's La Tilika,
like she jumped out of an icon
and straight into your hearts!
Ten, ten, ten, and ten!
A perfect score!
She's beaten Seta!
Looks like class two has
found their groove again!
[ARS] That's it for
the Granzia event!
Class two storms back
with a conditional spell
and claims the win
with fantastic teamwork!
Not too bad. Right, sir?
[ARS]
With that score, class two
has caught up with class one!
Incredibly,
this year's competition
is heading into the final
event in a dead heat!
Whoever wins these magic
duels is going to win it all!
[VELOS]
You haven't captured them yet?
No, Commander.
That magic instructor is aiding
the traitor's escape, sir.
[VELOS] You're using one
mage as your excuse?
You will find this
Rumia Tingel without fail.
And you will kill her.
[ARS] This duel's middle
bout has been intense,
with neither side ceding ground.
But wait!
The earth elemental
Gibul has summoned
has captured Kreiss,
and I'm not seeing
a counterspell!
I give up!
[ARS]
Kreiss admits defeat!
After Kash's loss
in the first round,
Gibul recovers with
a hard-fought victory,
and evens the score at one-one!
Nice! You just saved
our butts, Gibul!
[GIBUL]
Was there ever a doubt?
[ARS] And that brings us to
the final round, boys and girls!
Heinkel from class one
versus Sistine from class two,
with the match and the
overall title on the line!
It's about time I get to fight.
Hear the crowd?
I warmed them up.
Try not to waste that, Sistine.
Real motivational, Gibul.
Thanks for the support.
"If you win, we'll have a party.
I'll let you pig out on all the
food and drink you want."
Glenn told me to say that, too.
So, go on. Kick butt.
Yeah. You can count on me.
[SOLDIER 6B]
There they are!
[ARS]
Sistine is literally blown away
by Heinkel's
overwhelming Fire Wall!
[HALLEY]
Don't stop, Heinkel! Finish her!
Right.
[WENDY]
Hang in there, Sistine!
Think about the party!
We'll eat ourselves sick
on the professor's tab!
Don't be idiots. Win this.
Trust us, Sisti.
[SISTINE]
Do they think I don't know?
I'm no idiot!
Keep them all at bay.
Wall of tempest!
Grant peace to them below!
[HEINKEL]
She trapped me with wind!
What spell did she cast?
It's called Storm Wall.
She's using an altered spell?
Thunder sprites--
Too slow!
Pay heed, great wind!
[HEINKEL yells]
[ARS]
And it's over!
Sistine's Gale Blow has
thrown Heinkel out of bounds,
making class two the victors!
With those final points,
Professor Radar's team
wins it all!
[GROUP cheering]
[SOLDIER 6A]
It's over.
[ARS] Without further ado,
let's move on
to the award ceremony.
The winning team,
year two class two,
will now receive a medal from
Her Majesty the queen,
Alicia the Seventh!
Give it up for
this year's champion!
Uh...
Albert Frazer? Re=L?
You made it.
[ALICIA]
Huh?
Every year, the instructor
of the class
winning the magic
competition earns
an extremely special honor.
A big shiny medal
presented directly
by Her Majesty
the queen herself.
It was my only way
to get close to you.
[ALL gasp]
[SISTINE]
Professor! Rumia!
But how?
The Imperial Guard's
chasing you!
[GLENN] We swapped with
some friends along the way.
Just your basic Self Illusion.
I knew it!
That was Rumia!
Guards! Sieze them!
I don't think so.
[GUARDS yell]
That spell!
[GLENN]
Whoa. Isolation barrier.
Celica, you shouldn't have.
How dare you.
You're one to talk.
Commander Mutiny.
Sorry to interrupt
the party, Queen Alicia,
but your Imperial
Guard's been using
your good name to try
to kill an innocent girl.
Shut your mouth, vile traitor.
But luckily, you've had me
keeping Rumia safe.
And now the Guard's
outside this barrier.
So we're good!
Just order your men
to stop, Your Majesty.
And no one gets hurt.
That girl must die.
For what?
When this is over,
I'll take responsibility
for my failure.
And end my own life.
But I've sworn a vow.
To ensure the queen's
survival above all else.
It is my duty,
and Her Majesty's,
to preserve her life
for the sake of the empire,
no matter the sacrifice!
There's no time, my queen.
You must think
about your people
and make a decision.
This is my command.
You will put that girl,
Rumia Tingel, to the sword.
What?!
Forgive my bluntness,
but I cannot allow
that child to exist.
I wish she never had.
I have never loved her,
not one single day.
The only thing I regret
is giving birth to her at all.
If that is not true, nothing is.
I don't get this!
What the hell are you saying?
I know those are lies!
[RUMIA]
So that's it?
Is that all you have
to say to me?
Yes.
[RUMIA gasps]
[VELOS]
Thank you.
For your quick judgment,
my queen.
Celica! What is this?
[GLENN] Damn it!
This wasn't supposed to happen!
I thought getting here
was the answer!
What am I freaking missing?
[ALICIA] I figured she
wouldn't accept me.
Why would she
view me as her mother?
[GLENN] The queen doesn't
have to justify an execution.
Even if she thought
it was necessary
to protect the crown,
why would she say those lies?
What was the point?
[GLENN] Unless she wanted
me to catch the lie?
[CELICA]
I can't help you.
And I can't say anything more,
do you understand?
Whatever happens next
is up to you and you alone.
Could it be...?
[GLENN]
Your Majesty.
That's some necklace.
I couldn't help but notice it!
Why, thank you.
It's new, yet very
significant to me.
With a rock like that, I'm sure.
Wow!
But with all those karats,
it's gotta be heavy!
Why don't you take it off
and rest your shoulders?
Certainly not.
That's the last thing
I would want to do.
You don't say.
[VELOS]
Not another word, sorcerer.
[GLENN]
Rumia.
You can save the
tears for another time.
Your mom really does love you.
Get back!
[GLENN yells]
Professor!
[CELICA gasps]
Die!
No!
[VELOS]
My queen! What have you done?
[GLENN yells]
[GLENN]
A conditional-cursed necklace.
I love being right.
[GLENN]
Remove it and the wearer dies.
Time limit passes, wearer dies.
If anyone near it
explains the curse,
you guessed it, deadzo!
A classic ploy that's
been so overused
it's almost lame!
The only way to lift the
curse...
[GLENN]
Rumia had to die. Am I right?
I knew you'd solve it. There.
And did you know I was
gonna get a sword stuck
through my hand too?
Not cool.
Wait. But why didn't
the curse activate?
[VELOS]
The Fool Arcana?
What?
You mean you used that spell
to seal off the magic
that was in the necklace?
I had no idea.
[GLENN chuckles]
Now. Your Grace.
You can stop with the lies.
Huh? Lies?
[GLENN] She took a
big risk talking to us.
If she'd slipped up the curse
would've killed her.
Those lies were like
a riddle, a secret message,
helping me figure out the truth.
[ALICIA]
I'm so sorry, Ermiana.
I've done it again.
I've hurt you.
My queen?
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad you're safe.
[crying]
It's okay, Mom.
[BOTH crying]
[GUARDS gasp]
[SOLDIER 6F]
Her Majesty is safe!
The truth is that our superiors
assigned us two missions.
First, to monitor
the Imperial Guard,
which has lately shown
extremist tendencies.
Second, to the investigate
the backgrounds
of those closest to the queen.
Eleanor Chalet,
heretic mage with the
Researchers of Divine Wisdom.
You tried to orchestrate
the former princess's demise.
My question's why.
It seems the empire
isn't completely made up
of fools, after all.
Akashic Records, that's why.
Let's just say this.
That's what the princess is for.
You won't escape!
[GLENN]
Her handmaid, huh? Holy hell.
[ALBERT] Just proves how deep
the Researchers of Divine Wisdom
have burrowed into
the empire's core.
So you think there's
bound to be others, right?
[ALBERT]
We need to get back immediately
and plan countermeasures.
You be careful, too.
[GLENN chuckles]
Thanks for the
help today, Albert.
You're a real gem.
You too, Re=L.
Glenn. Next time
we'll settle things.
Right.
That a threat?!
[RUMIA]
Professor?
[GLENN]
How'd it go?
[CELICA]
Sure you can't stay?
[ALICIA]
Yes. But all is well.
I feel she was able to get
everything off her chest.
[ALICIA] I truly can't
thank you enough, Celica.
With you and
your apprentice here,
I know this is
the best place for her.
Please keep her safe.
And happy.
Sure.
That's what Glenn does best.
[RUMIA]
You were right.
I feel so much better
after talking to her.
That's yet another
thing I owe you for.
All I did was run around
and get stabbed.
Professor, how did
you figure it out?
That she was lying, I mean.
Three years ago...
Back when you were
abducted by those mages,
the queen asked me for help.
[ALICIA]
Please, I'm begging you, Glenn.
I know I shouldn't be
asking you to risk your life
on a rescue that
may be impossible.
But I... I just have to!
Please, Glenn,
she's everything to me!
The tears she cried,
you just can't fake.
I see. I wish I had known that.
So... You keep making
good on your promise.
I wasn't sure you
remembered it was me.
[GLENN]
There's still some bad guys.
So you can be as frightened
of me as you want,
but if you'll just stop crying,
then I can try to save you.
[RUMIA]
You said you were on my side.
Before you left, you promised
you always would be.
And you're still helping me,
some three years later.
A promise is
a promise, after all.
You know... All things
considered, I'm pretty lucky.
Both you and my mother
have saved me.
It all evens out,
'cause your class saved me.
Now I won the prize money
and three months salary
from Halbert, or whatever.
They deserve to
have a little party.
[STUDENTS]
Professor! Where've you been?
[SISTINE]
Hey!
There you guys are.
You're super late, you know!
[laughs]
Sisti, are you okay?
Yeah, she just had
too much brandy cake.
I think we all did, actually.
Hi, Professor.
Were you out helping Rumia?
You're always
taking care of her.
You're sweet when
you aren't a jerk!
[laughing]
Okay, white cat, that's enough.
I'm not catnip!
They just blew
the reward money
and three months salary
on one stupid dinner?!
[GLENN]
Okay, class, line up!
I've got an Extinction Ray
for every one of you ingrates!
[STUDENTS laughing]