[STUDENTS panting, sighing]
How far away is this lab?
You all right, Rumia?
I think I'm dying inside.
And Re=L...
She seems all right.
[SISTINE]
Hey, Re=L, you know,
we really freaked out when
we woke up this morning
and you weren't in the room.
You shouldn't sneak off
on your own so much.
I mean, if you keep breaking
the rules like that,
you might end up
like him someday.
Like Professor Radars.
[RE=L gasps]
--[SISTINE] Re=L?
--[RUMIA] Re=L?
[RUMIA]
Are you okay?
[RE=L]
Don't touch me again.
Hey, calm down.
She was trying to be nice.
[RE=L]
Shut up.
Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up, shut up!
Shut up!
All of you just
get away from me!
Re=L?
[RE=L]
I hate you both!
You're the worst!
Outta my way!
What was that?
You think she really
meant those horrible things
she said about us?
[GLENN]
Just ignore her.
[SISTINE]
Professor?
Right now, she's
a little unstable.
I said some stuff--
Stuff I definitely
shouldn't have,
and it kinda pissed her off.
My bad.
[GROUP gasps]
[chattering]
[BURKS] Ah, it's always
nice to see students
from the Alzano
Imperial Magic Academy.
Welcome to our white
alchemy research lab.
I'm the director here,
Burks Blaumohn.
Hey, there.
Thanks for helpin' us out
with our field research.
Nice place.
[BOYS snoring]
[GIRLS laughing]
[STUDENTS chattering]
We should just give
her some space for now.
[BURKS] White alchemy is a
field that combines alchemy
with white magic.
In this discipline,
we examine nothing less
than life itself.
That's why it's necessary
for us to be located here,
a place that's constantly
refilled with fresh mana.
[RUMIA gasps]
Hey, Rumia,
is something wrong?
Uh, oh, it's nothing.
[BURKS] Here we study the
hybridization of multiple plants
and animals to create what
are known as chimeras.
Wow! Amazing!
Intriguingly gross.
[SISTINE]
Wow, you know,
I was planning to major
in magic archaeology,
but after this, I'm starting
to seriously reconsider.
How 'bout you?
I'm aiming for mage
bureaucracy, so...
Besides, looking
around this place
makes me feel kind of...
[SISTINE]
Hm?
Well, it...
It makes me wonder
if it's really okay
for people to manipulate
life like this.
It seems wrong.
[SISTINE] True, if you were
to delve too deep into this...
...you could start down the
path to becoming an evil mage.
But from what I see,
it doesn't look like
they're doing that kind
of research here.
Thought it was pretty obvious,
but I guess not.
I'm talking about bringing
the dead back to life.
Way back when,
the empire initiated
an experiment
called "Project Revive Li--"
[BURKS] Ah, you know
your history well.
[GROUP chattering]
[BURKS] Must say, I'm
surprised a student your age
knows about that.
No big deal.
But one thing
I don't understand.
In all our classes,
we're taught that
resurrecting the dead
is theoretically impossible.
Precisely.
At the moment, no magic exists
that can disprove that axiom.
That's actually the very
reason why they founded
Project Revive Life.
[GLENN] They figured they
needed three ingredients.
A body created
through alchemy
using the dead guy's
genetic code,
which they cleverly
called a "Gene Code,"
an Astral Code,
which is just memories
transformed into data,
and Alter Ether,
which resets a person's spirit.
Those elements are
combined to revive someone.
'Least that was the theory.
Uh, Professor!
I appreciate the explanation,
but did you have
to butt in like that?
Oh, sorry 'bout that.
I just knew something
and wanted to prove it.
Essentially the idea is to
fuse together these elements
to create a facsimile
of the deceased.
Yeah, but in that case,
is it really even
a resurrection?
Indeed, that might not
be the best term for it.
More accurately,
it's creating a duplicate
of who they were
shortly before death.
[GLENN]
Relax.
That line of research
was abandoned
a long time ago.
See, the problem was
multiple chumps had to die
just to revive one person.
The lucky stiff, if you will.
That kinda trade-off
wasn't exactly sustainable.
Yes, too true.
We humans are not
meant to be gods.
Nothing gives us
the right to decide
who should live
and who should die.
Project Revive Life ought
to remain sealed away
in the dusty
archives of history.
Although, I've heard rumors that
the Researchers of
Divine Wisdom have stolen
and successfully completed
the project's core research.
Oh, come on,
you don't believe that.
It's just an urban legend.
Um, this is just
out of curiosity,
but aside from the
three elements
Professor Radars mentioned,
is there anything else
you can think of
that might be needed
to get Project Revive Life
to work?
The only thing that
comes to mind is
original magic.
If there was somebody who
possessed the original magic
necessary to Project
Revive Life, then maybe.
[SISTINE] But what are the odds
of someone showing up like that?
I mean they have to be
incredibly small, right?
[BURKS laughs]
That they are.
Regardless, the point is
successfully completing
that project
would require something that
makes the impossible possible.
Hey, there.
Kash and the others
invited us to dinner.
They're going to a
local place that serves
authentic island food.
Rumia?
[SISTINE]
Hey, Re=L.
Everyone's goin'
into town for dinner.
Wanna come?
It'll be fun--
No way.
[GLENN] Hey, why don't you
give it a rest already, Re=L?
You can't keep
sulking alone forever.
Shut up!
[GLENN]
What a brat.
[RE=L]
It's their fault!
It's all their fault!
They're the ones--who took
Glenn away from me.
I hate them!
[RE=L panting]
Why, Glenn?
Why? Why won't you?
[crying]
[GLENN]
Re=L is basically just a child.
Sure, she looks the
same age as you guys,
but mentally,
she's like a little girl.
And not the
brightest one, either.
We're talking the kind
that eats paint.
It's not her fault.
It's just the way she was born.
Anyway, hope you won't
lose patience with her
and run for the hills.
Believe me.
I know how tempting that'll be.
What? Don't be ridiculous!
Professor we would
never just abandon Re=L.
All right, I'm going to go
out there and look for Re=L!
Nah, you girls should
wait for her here
in case she comes back.
But what about...
[RUMIA, SISTINE gasp]
[GLENN] Don't worry,
I'll go look for Re=L.
I am her teacher.
So I kinda have to.
[RE=L crying]
[RAINER] Aw, why are
you crying, Re=L?
[RE=L]
Who's there?
Oh, I'm hurt.
You don't recognize
your big brother?
Is that you?
Wait, but how?
At last.
I've missed you so much.
[ALBERT]
Tsk. So that's the play?
A barrier to keep others out?
You work fast, don't you?
Or perhaps I was
just overly careless.
[ELEANOR laughs] Aw, are you
out here all alone tonight?
Poor boy.
[ALBERT] Well, I certainly
wasn't expecting you,
Eleanor Chalet.
You excited to see me?
Perhaps I could impose
on you to entertain me
for the night, Albert?
I promise to give
you one hell of a time,
fueled with a passion
so shameless and unbridled
it will make you scream
so loud you raise the dead.
[ALBERT]
Unfortunately for you,
I have no interest
in cheap women.
So get lost.
[ELEANOR laughs]
What a cold man you are.
I'm sure you're still
acting out some vile scheme
involving the princess
right now,
but it ends here.
I'm removing you from the board.
Immediately.
My, my, someone's impatient.
No need for such haste.
Flame lion!
Come forth,
red king of beasts!
[ELEANOR]
Come out.
Ah, come out, come out!
O, spirits of the night,
answer my call.
Answer.
Answer my call!
Console and moisten thyselves
with his flesh and blood!
Now. Rise up! Feast!
[laughing]
[ZOMBIES moaning, growling]
A necromancer!
[ZOMBIES growling]
Golden lightning beast,
pay heed,
race across the earth,
and dance to the heavens.
[ZOMBIES scream, moan]
Come forth,
and vanquish the dark.
[ZOMBIES screaming]
[ELEANOR giggles]
[ALBERT]
Ah, let me guess.
You thought that you
would have an easy time
besting me in close magic combat
simply because I'm a sniper.
[ELEANOR]
Oh, not at all.
It's just, you're so much
stronger and virile
than I imagined!
And so intense!
Oh, Albert, you're
driving me... crazy!
Your super regeneration--
It's not a conditional
healing spell or the result
of any drugs accelerating
your own healing factor.
No, it's something
far more repugnant.
[ELEANOR laughs]
[ALBERT] This woman is
on a whole different level
than any of the evil mages
I've eliminated before.
If I can manage to capture her,
the Empire will gain
a huge advantage
over her organization.
[ELEANOR] Shall we continue with
this evening's entertainment?
[ALBERT] No, she's too
dangerous to take any chances.
I have to finish her right
here and now, for good!
[RUMIA] So, what do you
think is wrong with Re=L?
[SISTINE]
I don't really know why, but...
When we went down
to the beach...
Friends, huh?
I don't get it,
but I think I could like it.
[SISTINE] I just don't
think Re=L was lying
when she said that.
Me, either.
[SISTINE]
All right!
I'm gonna go
pick up some food!
Those guys will probably
be starving to death
when they get back here.
[RUMIA giggles]
Yeah, good thinking.
[RE=L]
Brother...
It can't be. You're dead.
How are you here?
[RAINER] It's true the
organization killed me that day.
But, at the time,
you must've been so upset,
you didn't notice that
I was still breathing.
[RAINER]
Re=L, please save me.
Two years ago,
you managed to defect
and earn your own
freedom from them.
But meanwhile, I still
remain as their slave.
But... How can I do
anything to save you?
You know Rumia Tingel?
[RE=L gasps]
[RAINER] The organization
needs her for the plan
they have in motion right now.
Which means that mage, Glenn,
is a pretty big
obstacle for them.
The organization's
given me a chance.
If I can make this plan work...
...then I'll be free, Re=L.
Like you.
I don't know if...
Re=L...
I thought you were going
to protect your brother
no matter what.
[RE=L]
Yes. But I...
[RAINER] Or are you planning
to abandon me again?
[GLENN]
Re=L!
Re=L, get away from that man!
[RAINER gasps]
Glenn Radars?
Oh, so you've heard of me.
Just what I'd expect
from the Researchers.
[RAINER gasps]
No, I'm not...
Hey, Re=L.
I don't know what kinda
lies you've been filling
her head with,
but I do know that giving
me time to get here
was a big mistake,
you evil mage!
See, it doesn't matter
what fancy tricks
you've got up your sleeve.
Re=L, let's get this guy.
[GLENN gasps]
Huh? Really?
Thank you for everything.
Goodbye, Glenn.
I had to.
I have to live for
my brother's sake.
Pathetic!
Aw, sad!
Time to go.
Fire!
She got me good that time,
I'll admit it.
Oh, well.
I may have bought too much.
Though Professor Radars
does eat a lot.
Uh, Rumia?
Re=L? What have--
What have you done to her?
--[SISTINE] Rumia!
--[RE=L] Just relax.
I didn't kill her,
so don't panic.
She's just unconscious.
Wait a second.
[gasps] Hey, where is he?
The professor went
looking for you!
Oh, Glenn?
Yeah, I did kill him.
[SISTINE]
No. No way.
It can't be...
I don't understand.
Why would you do this?!
[RE=L]
'Cause I'm with the, um...
The Researchers of, um...
Oh, what was it again?
Anyway, I'm your enemy now.
And I'm taking Rumia with me.
[SISTINE]
Hold it right there!
You get away from her!
Do you hear me?
If you make a move, I'll shoot.
I said don't move!
Oh, will you?
Will you really do it?
[RE=L]
Go ahead.
I won't do anything to you.
[RE=L]
Shoot.
Bang. You're the opposite.
You act tough,
but you're just a child,
hiding your weakness
behind a mask.
Somebody help me!
[RE=L]
Shoot.
[RUMIA] I understand your point
about magic causing damage.
And make it truly
helpful to people.
[GLENN] If you're serious
about protecting Rumia,
this magic is your best bet.
Military-anything
isn't exactly cuddly.
But there's no way its
dark side is getting to you.
Your time is up.
[SISTINE]
How could I?
I had no choice.
If I'd fired,
I might have accidentally
hit Rumia, too.
And then there's Re=L.
She could've died.
At my hand.
[SISTINE]
No, that's not it.
I was just so scared,
I couldn't do anything.
[sobbing]
Professor...
[SISTINE gasps]
[ALBERT]
Sorry to barge in.
[SISTINE]
Mr... Frazer?
[SISTINE screams]
Professor Radars!
[ALBERT] Don't panic.
He's still breathing.
[SISTINE] He needs healing
magic right away!
Won't work.
He's already on the edge
of the reaper's scythe.
No, he...
Professor! Professor!
I need you to
share your strength.
What could you possibly
expect me to do?
If healing magic
won't work on him,
I can't help!
No!
No, no!
Why did this have to happen?
[crying]
Pull yourself together.
All this whining and self-pity
won't do anything to save him.
If you want to kill this man,
then by all means, keep crying.
Leave the rest
to the undertaker.
Wait, please don't go.
Just tell me.
What do you want me to do?
[SISTINE]
The white magic ritual, Reviver?
But doesn't that require an
enormous amount of mana?
Exactly.
That's why I'll be
using your mana, too.
Understood.
I'll handle the ritual's
complicated setup process.
You work the shortened,
temporary servant pact.
[ALBERT] He stopped
breathing. What a baby.
[SISTINE]
Huh?!
What? Professor?!
[ALBERT]
Calm down.
It's only his
breathing that stopped.
He still has a faint pulse.
Fibel, administer CPR
until the ritual's ready.
[SISTINE gasps]
CPR?
[ALBERT] If you're an academy
student, you should know how.
Yeah, but truth is,
I've never actually
performed it on--
Shut up and do it!
You don't have
time to be scared!
[RAINER]
Ah, you're awake now!
Sorry 'bout the rough treatment.
But we needed to get you
here, no matter what it took.
For our sake, as siblings.
Right, sis?
Wait, Re=L?
Why on earth are you doing this?
Where's Professor Radars?
Oh, he won't be
coming to save you.
Re=L murdered him in cold blood.
[RUMIA gasps]
He's lying.
Re=L.
You would never do that!
Would you, Re=L?
Tell me the truth!
[RE=L]
Sorry.