[CROWD cheering]
[ARS]
Incredible!
Class two comes from behind
in yet another event!
Who'dve imagined
these stunning results
at this year's
magic competition?
Professor Radar's class two has
cemented their dark horse status
as they continue
to climb up the board!
[ALBERT] So it's true.
That's our Glenn.
[RE=L]
No doubt about it.
He disappeared from our
ranks without saying a word.
And now we find him
playing teacher.
What is it, Albert?
Do you mind?
What do you plan to do, Re=L?
[RE=L] Settle the score
with him, of course.
Hey. What's your problem?
Don't you wanna confront him?
Naturally, there's a lot
I'd like to say to Glenn.
Still... Our mission
has to come first.
[RE=L]
Mission?
[ALBERT] We must oversee
the Imperial Guard
charged with protecting
Her Majesty, the queen.
[RE=L]
They're our allies.
Why are you concerned?
[ALBERT] We've received
word of suspicious activity
within the Guard.
There's a chance some
of them may try something
against Her Majesty.
That's what our
leadership tells me.
I see.
So I should take care of
this Glenn matter alone?
Is that what you mean?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GIRL giggles]
Man. They're rubbing
my face in it!
I'm so hungry I'm
about to eat this grass
like a damn dairy cow.
[LYNN]
Excuse me, Professor?
Huh?
[GLENN]
I'll try to help.
As long as it doesn't
involve money,
'cause I'm all out of that.
Well, sir...
It's about my next event.
Could I switch
with somebody else?
Let's see.
You're doing
transmutation, right?
[LYNN]
Yes.
I've been practicing
hard for it.
But I can't get the
Self Illusion spell down.
It just isn't working
for me, sir.
So you think someone
else could do better.
But that's not what you want.
I mean, you would rather
participate, right?
Don't you love transmutation?
Well, yes, sir.
I sure do. It's my favorite.
You get to become someone else!
So do it.
You'll be just fine.
[LYNN] But everyone's so excited
about how well we're doing
and winning it all with you.
I don't want to drag us down.
Huh?
That's what you're
worried about?
It's the magic competition.
It's for fun!
As long as you're
enjoying yourselves,
that's all that really matters.
[LYNN]
But Professor...
Okay, how's this?
We'll have a little
tutoring session.
To start, let's review
Self Illusion.
How would you
describe the spell?
It's black magic that cloaks
you in an illusion, sir.
[GLENN]
Exactly.
It's not some huge
spell that physically
reshapes your body--
it's just a trick.
Now behold.
Phantasmagoria.
Enacted by myself, I shall not
sing with another's voice.
There, you see?
It's really just a shell.
Then you can mold it
into whatever you want.
Amazing!
My guess?
The spell isn't working 'cause
you're thinking too vaguely.
You need to imagine
every detail.
Who are you trying to mimic?
The uh... Angel of Time,
La Tilika.
Nice.
Then find an illustrated
book on icons.
If you can visualize clearly
it should be a cinch.
You're more talented
than you think.
And even if you can't
pull it off today,
anyone who tries to blame
you for hurting our team
is getting a big helping
of my iron fist.
So, just relax and kick butt!
[LYNN giggles]
What's so funny?
I'm sorry.
Your words out of
Rumia's mouth are bizarre.
But honestly, Professor...
Thanks. I'll do my best.
Sounds good.
[LYNN giggles]
[SISTINE]
Rumia!
There you are!
[SISTINE]
We'd better hurry and eat!
I've got both our portions
from the class feast!
[RUMIA (GLENN) gasps]
Do you know where
that weirdo teacher went?
Haven't seen him in a while.
[GLENN]
Control yourself, Glenn!
A teacher tricking a
student out of her lunch?
That's eight kinds of wrong!
But it's a basket of heaven!
Hungry, Rumia?
Guess you worked up an appetite.
Yeah! I seriously might die if
I don't eat something quickly.
[SISTINE]
You're literally drooling.
[GLENN]
It's okay, I won't eat it all.
Just a small bite.
To, uh, check for poison.
Gotta protect these kids!
Get in my body!
[RUMIA]
Sisti, there you are!
Sorry I kept you--Uh...
Whoa.
Hey, there's two of me.
Wow. It's a real mystery
of the universe, huh?
Power, return to zero.
Welp, gotta go!
--You stupid idiot!
--[GLENN screaming]
What kind of teacher
masquerades as a student
just to steal her lunch?!
Calm down, Sisti.
I woke up extra early
today to make that!
[growls]
He ruined it!
[RUMIA giggles]
Gotta hand it to white cat.
Her distance is impressive.
[stomach growls]
[CROWD cheering]
[GLENN] Man, I don't know
what's wrong with me.
Feels like I keep sinking lower
on the human decency scale.
[RUMIA]
Professor!
[RUMIA giggling]
I figured you must be starving
to try a stunt like that.
So dig in.
Oh, thank you,
you sweet, freaking angel!
These tears are pure
liquid happiness!
Ah, I love the
tomato sweetness!
With the salty, savory ham!
And the earthy, nutty richness
of the thinly-sliced cheese.
It's like a perfect
harmony of flavors!
Awesome!
Did you make this yourself?
Me? Oh, no.
Truth is, in the kitchen,
I'm pretty much all thumbs.
Then who's the chef?
Sorry, but I can't tell you.
I've been sworn
to secrecy on that.
I'll just say...
This person woke up early
to make something special
for the class,
and for a certain man.
They got into a fight,
so she couldn't.
She was so mad she was
about to throw it away.
But I didn't want it
to go to waste.
Hmm. Nice.
So I'm better than a trash can.
I kinda feel bad
for the girl, though.
Sounds like the
guy's a major jerk.
I mean how can you
have a fight with someone
who just made you a
super-delicious sandwich?
Not cool.
That's a total bastard move.
[RUMIA laughs]
Jeez, now I'm stuffed!
Thanks for that.
It's a meal for the ages.
You're welcome.
The chef will be
happy you liked it.
We should probably
get back to the stadium.
[ALICIA] Actually, may we
speak for a moment?
You're Glenn.
Glenn Radars, correct?
That's me, but sorry,
I'm all out of moments.
Now that my belly's
not eating itself,
I have to--[gasps]
Holy crap! The queen!
[ZELOS]
Where has Her Majesty gone?
[SOLDIER 5A] I only took my eyes
off her for a minute, Commander.
You fool!
Just find her or else, soldier!
[SOLDIER 5A]
Yes, sir!
See that, Headmaster?
That guard's so freaked out I
think his brain might explode.
I can't believe you
had the gall to hide her
with your magic.
You're as terrifying a
woman as ever, Celica.
[CELICA chuckles]
Um, m'lady...
What's up, Eleanor?
There's something
I'd like to tell you.
It's sensitive, I'm afraid.
[CELICA gasps]
[ALICIA]
It's been a year now.
Have you been well?
Uh, peachy, Your Majesty.
Please raise
your head, good sir.
Ever since that day,
I've wished I could
apologize to you.
You bravely devoted yourself
to protecting this empire.
And so it shames me
you were expelled
from the Court Mage Corps
in such a disgraceful fashion.
[GLENN]
No, no! No shame!
I-I just quit 'cause I got
sick of the work, that's all!
You can't be lowering
your queenly head
to a world-class failure
like me, Your Majesty!
Now, Glenn...
Uh, but more importantly,
why are you here without
your guards, Your Grace?
[ALICIA] It's been such
a long time, Ermiana.
How are you, my dear?
I can't believe how
tall you've gotten.
How are the Fibels?
Do you like living
with their family?
[chuckles] It's surreal...
being able to see you again.
[ALICIA]
Ermiana.
Your Grace.
I beg your pardon.
I don't mean to be rude,
but there's been a mistake.
My name's Rumia.
Rumia Tingel, Your Grace.
I have no right to
contradict you, Majesty.
But it seems to me
that you may have somehow
confused me with the
late Princess Ermiana.
[ALICIA]
Yes.
Of course.
Ermiana's gone.
She died three years ago
from an epidemic.
I'm confused by grief.
My apologies for
putting you through
such unpleasantness, Rumia.
[RUMIA]
No apology needed, Your Grace.
Now if you'll excuse me.
[ALICIA] I figured she
wouldn't accept me.
Why would she view me
as her mother now?
[ALICIA]
I'll be going back now, Glenn.
[GLENN]
Uh, yes, Your Majesty.
[ALICIA] Promise me
you'll take care of her.
I will.
[ZELOS]
My queen.
Hello, Commander Zelos.
I hope I didn't worry you.
[ZELOS]
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
But I'm afraid I must insist
that you come with us.
[ALBERT]
I can't believe it.
The Imperial Guard is
treating their own queen
like a prisoner.
I didn't think they would dare.
Zelos, the Imperial Guard's
General Commander.
They say he fought
on par with the legendary
swordsman Johannes
in the Divine War
forty years ago.
Hardly the type
I'd expect to be rash.
Where are you going?
To dispose of our enemies.
The soldiers who make up
the Imperial Guard
are hand-selected for
their loyalty to the crown.
I find it hard to believe
they would harm the queen.
No, they must be plotting
something different.
[RE=L]
How's this for a strategy?
I'll charge in with
a full frontal assault.
Then you follow me after
with a full frontal assault.
[CROWD cheering]
[ARS] And Teresa from class two
clears 50 kilograms!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[GLENN] The former princess,
wiped from existence
'cause of her
special gifts, huh?
[SISTINE]
Professor.
What, white cat?
Gonna launch me again?
Oh, calm down!
I won't.
It's about Rumia--
she hasn't come back.
Do you have any idea
where she could be?
Okay, lean in, kitty.
What? Be serious!
[GLENN] Anybody would
want some alone time
after a suck-fest like that.
Guess I should
go look for her.
I hate the idea of
expending all that energy,
but she'll feel better
if she's with her friends.
Can you handle things
here while I'm gone?
Yeah, sure.
Please find her. I'm worried.
Hey, relax.
After that party in my stomach,
I could search for her all day.
I am in the zone!
Huh?
The merciful
Angel of Hunger Rumia
brought me some
sandwiches earlier.
I don't know who made them,
and they were
headed for the trash,
but hey, you can't beat free!
[SISTINE gasps]
Huh. I see.
And you ate them all, huh?
Well, congratulations.
You're a human dumpster.
You can't shame me.
They were delicious!
They weren't some
gastronomic miracle,
but they were tasty as hell!
And shame on you,
with your "dumpster" comment.
Some girl spent a
lot of time on those.
I thought you were
only mean to me,
but to imply her
sandwiches were trash?
I... That's not what I meant!
Just go and find Rumia, okay?
[GLENN]
What ya got there?
Professor.
This locket...
There's nothing inside.
But I feel like
there used to be.
Maybe a portrait
of someone special.
Someone precious.
Does that make me weird?
Wearing this every day
because of a picture
I just imagine is there?
Not really.
Like with spells,
it's about what the words
and tokens mean to you.
I'd say.
Professor, you know
the truth, don't you?
That Her Majesty and I...
Yeah.
Do you think I was wrong?
The way I handled
that situation?
The truth is I understand
why she did it.
She had to.
I'm one of the gifted,
to put it kindly.
Others would say
I'm the devil incarnate.
Or even cursed.
Because of this ability
I was born with,
I could become
a dangerous liability,
and rip the royal family apart.
So of course.
I know it was necessary.
The queen had to erase me.
She couldn't put
the empire at risk.
But even though it makes sense,
part of me can't
forgive what she did.
Part of me feels
so mad I could scream.
[GLENN] Can't apply logic
to matters of the heart.
[RUMIA] But another
part of me just wants
to call her "Mother"
one more time.
Wants to hug her,
and be hugged so tight.
But then...
I think about Sisti's parents,
how they've taken me in
with no questions
asked and treated me
like their own.
And that makes me feel
like I'm betraying them.
I'm lost.
How do I reconcile all that?
Here's my philosophy.
Human beings are regretful
by nature. Always.
Any choice we make comes
with pain no matter what.
[GLENN] It's easy to
say "pick carefully,"
so you won't have regrets.
That's a load of bull.
You agonize over
the path you choose,
but you'll always find
time to think of the turns
you didn't take.
It's the pain and the joy
of the human experience.
My advice?
Just make sure you're
being honest with yourself.
Honest?
Yeah.
'Cause the closer you can
get to your true feelings,
the less those regrets down
the line are gonna hurt.
Rumia.
What do you want most of all?
That's just it.
Right now I'm not sure
what I'm feeling.
A long time ago,
I served in the
Imperial Army as a mage.
Due to the nature
of my assignments,
I visited the court
pretty often.
Every time I went, I would
see the most powerful person
in the kingdom wearing a locket
just like the one you're
holding in your hand.
She may have erased
you from the books,
but not from her heart.
So does that locket
have meaning?
Hell yeah, it does.
Even if it's just to
unload your resentment.
Start by confronting her.
Tell the queen all those
feelings you told me about
instead of running away from it.
You think so?
'Course.
I'm hardly the person to talk
after all the running I've done.
But... I'm scared.
Her eyes can turn so cold,
and I'm not sure
I could handle that.
Do you think you could...
Do you think you could go
with me, Professor Radars?
Damn it.
All right.
I'm such a softy.
Great! I can't thank you enough!
[GLENN]
Speaking of the Guard.
[SOLDIER 5A]
Are you Rumia Tingel?
Yes, that's right
I hereby declare...
You are accused of
conspiracy to assassinate
Queen Alicia the Seventh!
And found guilty!
You will be executed immediately
for this heinous treason
against the Crown!
[RUMIA]
What? Me?
Assassinate the Queen?
Is this some
crappy performance art?
Where's your proof?
It's not your
business, outsider.
You're going to execute
her with no warrant
and no trial?
[SOLDIER 5A]
Yes.
By direct order of Her Majesty.
Cut the crap!
Step away from her, fool!
If you continue to defend her,
then you'll be executed
for treason, as well.
[RUMIA]
I surrender.
Are you nuts?
I'm the queen's subject.
If Her Majesty accuses
me of betraying her,
then it's my duty to pay
for that sin with my life.
But please.
Don't hurt my professor.
Shut up! What are you do--
Professor!
[SOLDIER 5A]
Let's go.
Close your eyes and don't move,
for your own sake.
If I miss your heart, it will
only prolong your suffering.
Yes.
[RUMIA] I always thought
this would happen.
That one day she'd
decide to finish the job,
and take my life.
[RUMIA]
Of course.
That's why she came to see me.
To say goodbye.
I was supposed to die that day,
but I was given
three more years,
and created so many
wonderful memories.
[RUMIA]
Don't be sad. Be grateful.
[GLENN]
Keep those eyes shut, okay?
[SOLDIERS grunt]
[SOLDIER 5C]
I'm blind!
[GLENN] Aw, jeez, sword
hilts are a bitch.
[RUMIA]
Professor!
What have you done?
What? It's just a
Flash a Light spell.
They're blind, not dead.
But why?!
Why did you rescue me?
Well, if I hadn't, white cat
would've yelled my ears off.
[RUMIA]
This isn't funny!
Now they're gonna
convict you, too!
I had to. I promised.
Well, relax we'll
straighten this out.
The queen would never have
ordered your execution,
let alone without a trial!
There's no way that makes sense.
I don't know what's going on,
but there's a bigger
knot to untie.
We just need to figure
out how to talk to her.
[SOLDIER 5D]
Over there!
You're going to be
sorry, traitors!
Professor, what are
we going to do now?
Now we freaking run!
Great rule of time.
Balance of the scales.
Let the plate of
order tip portside.
[SOLDIER 5D]
Don't let those rebels escape!
[GLENN] Why do I keep
getting crap thrown at me?
People love to make fun
of the unemployed shut-ins,
but dudes don't run
after them with swords!
--[RUMIA] What's your plan?
--[GLENN] Excellent question!
How can we slip
past the Imperial Guard,
but still get face time
with the Queen?
Wait...
It doesn't have to be
our faces, does it?
I think it's time to grow
this supposed conspiracy.
[CELICA]
Glenn?
Yeah, hey, Celica.
You're sitting with
Her Majesty, right?
I need help, okay?
[CELICA]
I can't help you.
Excuse me? I haven't asked yet!
You don't have to.
Now listen to me carefully.
I can't help you.
And I can't say anything more,
do you understand?
Don't suppose I'm lucky
and you're joking?
[CELICA]
No.
[GLENN]
And our situation?
[CELICA]
I have a rough idea.
So is this some kind of
mutiny by the Imperial Guard?
Or does Her Majesty
actually want Rumia dead?
Let me guess, you can't say.
[CELICA]
No. You're on your own.
[GLENN]
What?
Whatever happens next
is up to you and you alone.
Please, take those
words to heart.
Find some way
to do what's right,
and present yourself
to the queen.
Hey, wait!
Damn it.
Professor?
[GLENN] What was that,
some kind of riddle?
Present myself to the queen?
She's surrounded by
highly-trained soldiers.
Not to mention Commander Zelos.
Gimme a break.
This is obviously way
above my pay grade.
How do I do this?
It's you?!