[SISTINE gasps]
No more, please, Professor.
I'm so sore.
That's just because
it's your first time.
The more we do this,
the better you'll get.
I hope you're right.
It feels like
I still have so much
to learn, though.
[GLENN] Hey, being hard
on you is my job.
And I say you've already
improved since we started.
[GLENN] Make sure you
stay warm and supple.
We could both get hurt
if you're too tight.
[SISTINE]
It smells like the Professor.
I have just one more
question, Professor.
Why are we doing
hand-to-hand combat?!
I'm glad I finally
got you hot and bothered
enough to ask me that!
[chuckles]
"Special training."
I thought I'd learn new spells.
Or that maybe you would teach me
how to boost my magic powers.
But by training in this way,
we hone your sense of when to
attack or defend in magic duels.
[SISTINE] Or you're just
putting me through all this
because you think
I nag too much.
Of course, that's part of it.
I hate you!
Good! Channel it into your
hand-to-hand combat,
because once you've
got it going on there,
we're moving on to
military-grade magic.
Military magic?
Don't be scared.
I know it's intimidating,
but if you're serious
about protecting Rumia,
this magic is your best bet.
So buck up.
I know military-anything
isn't exactly cuddly.
But I'm confident
you can master this.
There's no way its dark
side is getting to you.
Well, at least I don't think so.
These things can still
be pretty tricky.
I wish to continue
my training with you!
Thank you, Professor!
[RUMIA] Oh, hey, good morning,
Professor Radars.
Yeah, yeah, hey.
Professor, you look like
death eating a cracker.
He's so worried
about you, Rumia,
he waits here every day
to check in.
Isn't that right?
No, it's not that.
You don't have
to worry, Professor.
Things are all back
to normal now.
I'm just sitting here.
It's a coincidence,
nothing more.
[GLENN yells]
[RUMIA, SISTINE gasp]
We need to talk, "Professor."
What... the hell?!
You coulda killed me!
What's your deal?!
I'm greeting you?
How the hell was
that a greeting?!
But Albert said
this what I should do
when reuniting with
an old comrade in arms.
So he's behind this?
We had our differences,
but not like that!
That's the girl from
the magic competition.
Your name is Re=L, right?
Does the uniform mean you're--
Oh, yeah, wait...
You're the new student here?
What's going on here?
The Imperial bigwigs
decided Rumia would be safest
with her own bodyguard.
The plan was to send in
a mage undercover
as a new transfer student.
But I never thought
they'd pick you!
You came here
just to protect me?
That's so sweet.
I hope we can
become close friends.
Me, too.
But I'm here to protect him.
Rumia needs the
body-guarding, not me!
The cute blonde girl I'm
pointing at on your left!
Okay?
No, not okay.
I don't want to protect her.
I want to protect you, Glenn.
I'm already sick
and tired of you!
[RE=L]
Ow. Stop it.
And now that we're
clear on that point,
under no circumstances
are you allowed
to expose your identity
or the mission here!
Ever! You got that, Re=L?!
Will this work?
I have no idea.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Uh, class, we have
a new student joining us.
Re=L Rayford.
So, um, you know,
don't bully her or whatever.
Now she'll tell us
about herself. Go.
My name is Re=L.
I just said that, dumbbell!
Talk about your
hobbies or interests.
Something normal and relatable.
Roger that.
My name is Re=L Rayford.
I'm enlisted in
the Imperial Army,
assigned to Imperial Court
Mage Corps, Special Forces--
Shut up!
When I grow up,
I will enlist in
the Imperial Army.
Oh, and I was born...
She is such a weirdo.
[STUDENT 6A]
I think she's kinda cute.
Great. Now go sit down.
[WENDY]
Um, can I ask a question?
What?
So, are you like a runaway?
Or did you move
with your family?
I have a brother.
Well, had.
Uh, okay!
Please refrain from asking
questions about her family.
Seeing as she has none.
[WENDY, TERESA gasp]
I'm so sorry.
I had no idea.
[KASH]
Question!
I'm getting the vibe you two
have a prior relationship
of some kind.
What's the deal?
--[STUDENTS gasp, chatter]
--My relationship with Glenn?
Well... It's complicated.
[STUDENTS gasp, chatter]
Glenn is the light of my life.
Everything I do is
for him and only him.
Oh, that is so romantic!
She's dating the teacher?!
What? No!
Why would you say that?!
--[STUDENTS chattering]
--[RUMIA chuckles]
Thunder sprites, shock!
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--[SISTINE] Yes!
You've really been
practicing, haven't you!
White cat, nice!
Landing all six shots
from back there
takes some real skill.
Oh. It was easy.
Okay, next.
That means you, Re=L, c'mon.
All right. Here we go!
She's gotta be pretty talented
if she's joining the Army.
Thunder sprites, pay heed,
and strike with your
electric shock.
[GLENN] I've never actually seen
Re=L use Shock Bolt before,
but damn, I didn't think
she'd be this bad.
So, uh, she's an Imperial Mage?
Maybe she's just nervous?
Heads up. You got one shot left.
Am I allowed to use a spell
other than shock bolt?
I guess so, yeah.
But Shock Bolt's the only
one students can handle
that hits from back here.
[RE=L]
So any spell is fine?
Look, just do it.
Okay, great.
[GLENN]
But no military magic!
[RE=L]
I beseech creation!
Grant unto my hands
a great and powerful blade!
[STUDENTS gasp]
No, Re=L, stop it!
[RE=L yells]
Six out of six.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[RUMIA chuckles]
[GLENN]
Great.
Now they think she's
weird and dangerous!
Hey, Re=L?
What're you doing for lunch?
I don't eat lunch.
I can go for three days
without any food.
Okay, but don't you
find it hard to function
when you don't eat?
Good point.
[RUMIA] Well, Sistine and I
are going to the cafeteria
and we'd love if you joined us.
[RE=L]
Cafeteria?
[STUDENTS chattering]
What do you think? Nice?
There are a lot of people.
[sniffs]
And good smells.
Come on! Let's go order!
I'm getting my usual.
What about you?
Do you want that?
Or would you rather have
the same thing as me?
[RUMIA giggles]
Okay. Strawberry tart it is!
[RUMIA]
Wow, you really like it.
--[RE=L] Yes.
--[RUMIA] I knew you would.
Sisti loves them, too.
Want some? I have plenty.
[SISTINE]
Uh...
Uh, no, thanks.
I'm pretty stuffed.
I won't touch them, I promise.
You sure?
[SISTINE]
Mm-hmm!
[RUMIA giggles]
You've got cream all over.
Hold on, I'll help.
Get you all cleaned up.
There! Now you're good as new!
Thank you.
Just slow down
and you'll be fine.
We couldn't help but
notice that you three
have gotten close.
She's so cute.
You'd never believe
she's the girl
who used military magic.
No one's gonna take your tarts!
It's all right.
No need to rush, sweetie.
[GLENN] So, leaving Rumia's
protection in Re=L's hands...
What exactly is the
military thinking there?
I hear she is quite
the odd-banana.
Oh, yeah.
But, then, maybe going
back to school
will help her be more social.
Isn't it also
her teacher's job
to help with that sort of thing?
Maybe.
I do have high hopes she
might learn a thing or two
on our upcoming
class field trip.
Provided I can pull it off.
[CELICA chuckles]
Well, it sounds like you're
going for teacher of the year.
[GLENN]
Shut up.
Anyway, what're you
in here reading now?
Hm? Oh, this?
Nothing.
[KASH groans]
This blows.
I wish we could go to
Canturley's research lab.
That would have been
an awesome field trip.
These field trips
always just come down
to luck of the draw.
Don't worry, fellas.
You are definitely in luck.
This'll be the best
field trip yet!
[GROUP gasps]
Boys, tell me.
Where's the Alchemy
Research Lab located?
Ah! Cineria Island!
Famous for its
sandy beaches, sir!
Correct!
And Cineria Island
is warm year-round,
which means even
now people there
are wearing only
their bathing suits!
What? Bathing suits?!
And every girl in this
class is total smoke-show.
[STUDENTS gasp]
See what I'm gettin' at?
So shut up and follow me!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[cheering]
Boys can be such idiots.
And our teacher's their leader.
[GIRLS giggling]
Well, hello, ladies!
I've got the perfect curios
for you fine cuties!
Now, girls, this is
a school field trip,
not a shopping trip for
crappy knickknacks.
--[STUDENT 6A] But...
--[GLENN] Go on.
[STUDENTS]
Aww.
[ALBERT (SALESMAN)]
"Crappy" is inappropriate.
Each one of these
is a rare artifact
from the Alzano Imperial family!
All right,
that's enough, Albert.
Wait, if you're shadowing Rumia,
Re=L's a decoy?
That's right.
I'm the real bodyguard,
deep in the shadows.
I called it.
So, I assume you
wouldn't blow your cover
unless you had something to say.
Be careful of Re=L.
She's a dangerous girl.
Hey, that's not funny, Albert.
[ALBERT] You know it's
the truth. We both know.
All of that is in the past now.
You're still so naïve.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Cineria Island, wow!
[GLENN gasps]
Should we get a bucket?
Glenn, you look awful.
Uh, Professor,
are you gonna be okay?
Since you get seasick,
we should've picked
a different place.
Like Canturley's Army
Mage Research Lab.
I'm here for girls
in bathing suits,
and that's all that matters.
Am I right, boys?
Even if this island were smack
in the middle of a warzone,
I'd still've brought us here!
[STUDENTS] We'll follow
you anywhere, Professor!
[RE=L]
Hm?
Just ignore those idiots.
C'mon, let's go explore.
You wanted to get us
away from military magic,
didn't you?
That's why you chose this place.
You're overthinking it.
I just want to see
you all in bikinis.
Yoo-hoo! Sisti! Re=L!
Hurry up, I'm over here!
I'm coming!
[SISTINE]
Wanna swim with us, Re=L?
[RE=L]
Sure.
[GIRLS laughing]
It's just like I told ya:
Good things happen when
you shut up and follow me!
Thank you!
You got till sundown!
Go have fun, fellas!
Yes, sir!
[laughing]
[GLENN yawns]
Would it kill you to
have some fun, Gibul?
[GIBUL]
I am having fun.
I didn't think we came here
to play on the beach.
Hey, you.
How do I look?
Whoa, you look great, Rumia.
Rock that bikini bod!
Oh, Professor Radars,
you're so sweet.
[GLENN]
White cat.
I like your style
with that sarong.
Provocative.
Thanks, but could you please
not stare at me like that?
[GLENN]
Mm-hmm.
Stop.
What's wrong?
Nothing, Glenn.
Why don't you guys go
play a game or something?
Actually, we're about to
start a volleyball tournament.
You want in, Professor Radars?
Beach volleyball, huh?
I just hate how
it hurts your hand.
All right, jerks! Let's do this!
Invisible hand.
Take that!
[STUDENTS laughing, chattering]
[KASH] Now for the best part
of every overnight field trip:
Sneaking into the hotel
and peeping on the girls!
[KY]
You sure this'll work?
[KASH]
Of course!
I've already scouted the
whole route multiple times.
Always prepared.
Nice work, Kash.
What about Professor Radars?
Don't worry, Ky.
I've run all the numbers.
The chances of him
walking by are near zero.
Oh, man. We're doing this!
All right, guys!
Ready to make this
the best field trip ever?
[ALL]
Mm!
[GLENN] Sorry, boys,
but your little plan won't work.
Uh, what?!
How long have you been there?
Morons!
If I were you guys,
I would--Go there.
And then here.
Then through that.
If I was going to sneak
into the girls' hotel room.
[ALL sigh]
You had us scared.
It's too bad you broke curfew.
Go back in.
There are times when
a man can't back down!
And this is one of them!
We've come too far
to give up now!
We're growing boys! With needs!
[GLENN] I see.
You're not about to back down.
And as your teacher,
I have no choice
but to remove you by force.
And we'll do whatever
it takes to stop you
so we can see boobs!
Let's blast him!
Bring it on, horndog!
[ALL yelling]
[SISTINE] Again, I'd like
to point out the boys
are huge idiots.
I've never seen Glenn
have so much fun.
Oh, yeah?
He's like this all
the time at school.
Well, he used to
be way gloomier.
That's why I thought it so
important I stay close by.
Y'know, to protect him.
Uh, you okay?
C'mon, girls!
You ready to play some cards?
Re=L. We saved a seat for you!
[RE=L] You really
want me to play cards?
Yeah!
Okay.
I don't get it, but I'll play.
[WENDY giggles]
Great, you can shuffle.
I think she's finally
starting to fit in.
Yeah.
You're right.
[BOYS groaning]
[GLENN]
Ah! Ow, ow, ow!
Those guys don't know
how to pull their punches.
Well, here's to a good time.
[RUMIA laughs]
Oh, wow.
So pretty!
Re=L?
You gotta love that view.
Come on.
[RE=L] I'm not really
sure about much, but
I don't think
I'll ever get tired
of this view tonight.
That's great.
We're so happy we've
gotten to know you, Re=L.
Why's that?
'Cause we like you!
[RUMIA] You're not the new girl
anymore. You're our friend.
We're friends now?
[RUMIA giggling]
[SISTINE shrieks, laughs]
I'm gonna get you!
[RE=L]
Friends, huh?
I don't get it, but I
think I could like it.
[GIRLS laughing]
[GLENN] What did Albert
mean by "be careful"?
Re=L is a normal-ish girl.
[yawns]
[GLENN]
What are you doing out here?
I wanted to talk to you, Glenn.
Okay, let's go in.
[RE=L]
Hey.
Why did you leave?
You know why, but look.
I do feel guilty about up
and quiting the mage corp.
I didn't mean to
hurt you like that.
You realize that
without you around,
I don't have anything
to live for.
There's no point.
What?! Re=L, that's not
true and you know it!
You were just with
Rumia and white cat.
The whole damn class!
[RE=L]
But I don't get it.
Why don't you just
start over and become
a real student here?
Wash your hands of
the Imperial Mage Corps.
Listen!
I live for you, Glenn!
No, you don't!
If your brother was still here,
he'd want you living
your own life!
[RE=L]
I don't get it.
I don't understand anything
you're saying, Glenn!
Why do you think it's so wrong?!
Whoa, hey, hey!
--Calm down.
--No! Don't tell me that!
What's wrong with
protecting you?!
What's so wrong with
you staying by my side?!
I hate it!
Hey, Re=L...
Sistine. Rumia.
It's like they stole you
away from me, isn't it?
Why the hell would
you ever think that?
Shut up, Glenn, shut up!
This is all their fault!
I hate them!
--I hate them all!
--[GLENN] Re=L, wait a sec!
[GLENN] Things never
work out how I think.
[ELEANOR] I assure you,
our organization
is actively looking
into the matter.
[LAINEL]
Excellent.
We've already made
preparations for the Amplifier.
That's good to hear.
We are about to find
that which we both seek.
[chuckles]