[SISTINE]
Please don't tell me
you're with the Researchers
of Divine Wisdom!
How dare you!
You worthless little bitch!
Don't try to lump me
in with that pathetic
little club of low-life garbage!
[LEOS]
Anyway.
I think you're clever
enough to understand.
You don't have the
right to turn me down.
[SISTINE]
Professor, I...
[KASH]
Hey, did you hear?
About Sistine?
Accepting Professor
Kleitos's proposal?
Yeah, the ceremony's next week.
That's awfully soon, isn't it?
[GIBUL] I thought that
they were already engaged.
So why is everybody
making a fuss now?
Honestly...
I'm more interested in finding
out why Professor Radars
never showed up for that duel.
[WENDY]
Sistine! Is it true?
Are you seriously
getting married?
Yes.
What happened to becoming a
magic archaeologist, though?
Isn't that what you wanted?
Oh, that.
That was just a dream.
I have to face reality now.
[WENDY] Are you really just
gonna let your best friend
throw away her future like this?
I don't think...
[LEOS]
Hey, sweetie.
We have wedding
plans to discuss.
Care to come with me?
[SISTINE]
Uh, sure. Let's go.
[LEOS chuckles]
Please excuse us.
[RE=L]
Rumia, can I cut him down?
I don't know how,
but I know he's bad!
[RUMIA]
No!
Rumia?
[RUMIA]
You can't do that.
Yeah, but...
[RUMIA]
Please, be patient.
I'm sure Professor Radars
will think of something.
But Glenn is gone.
Who knows where he is...
or if he'll be back.
[RUMIA]
I tried to ask Sisti about it
when she came home that night,
but all she would say is
that she's marrying Leos.
[SISTINE]
Just leave me alone, okay?
Sisti...
What the hell do you want?
Rumia?
Professor, if we don't
do something, Sisti will...
[RUMIA] I told Professor
Radars everything I knew--
everything that had happened.
And then...
I've got this.
[RUMIA] Right after that,
he went to Re=L
and told her that
she should stay with me.
Then he just disappeared.
[RUMIA]
It'll be all right.
He assured me that
he had it all covered,
so have faith and
just wait for him.
[bells ringing]
[door opens]
Rumia.
Re=L.
[RUMIA]
Sisti, you look so beautiful!
Pretty.
That frilly outfit,
it'd be hard to fight in,
but I want it.
[SISTINE]
Don't worry.
I'm sure someday
you'll get to wear one
of your own.
Hey, Sisti...
The ceremony's about to start,
so you should go find a seat.
[RUMIA]
Sisti.
[SISTINE crying]
[PRIEST 12A]
Do you, Leos Kleitos,
take this woman to be your wife,
to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better or for worse...
[WENDY] There's not a single
person on the groom's side.
That's not weird to anyone?
[PRIEST 12A]
...to love and to cherish,
until death do you part?
I do.
[LEOS] Now let's talk about
your friend Rumia Tingel's
real name and power.
And that science experiment,
Re=L Rayford.
Do you care enough
to do what it takes
to save them?
I do.
[PRIEST 12A]
You may now kiss the bride.
[GLENN] Get your filthy
peter clamps away from her!
I object to this marriage!
Was waiting for you
to get to that part,
but you skipped right over it!
And I sure as hell
ain't gonna hold my peace!
Suck smoke!
--Nice!
--Awesome!
[WENDY]
I knew he'd come!
Re=L, protect Rumia!
I'm on it.
Oh, wow!
[GLENN]
You may now kiss my ass!
[GROUP cheering]
[SISTINE]
Let go of me this instant!
I mean it!
Put me down, right now!
This is no picnic
for me, either.
Y'know, you're a lot
heavier than you look.
There.
[SISTINE]
You've ruined everything!
Take me back,
I have to marry Leos!
If I don't, then...
Lemme guess.
He was using Rumia
to threaten you?
Yeah, I figured it had
to be something like that.
Then you just left me.
Where have you been
all this time?
I thought...
I thought you'd...
Sorry.
Got held up.
[GLENN] After Rumia
told me what was going on,
I tried thinking of ways
I could bring you back.
Only thing I knew for sure was
I'd be the one on the losing end
if I didn't take
the fight seriously.
That was it.
[GLENN] Feels like I'm
back in the old days.
Wonder how well this
little toy of mine'll
work on him.
Well, regardless,
I just need to lure
Leos out to where I have
the upper hand,
and then kick his ass.
[GLENN] So, what do you
think Leos's end game is?
I've been wracking my brain
trying to figure it out,
but nothing really jumps at me.
Best I could come up with
is that he loves you so much,
he'd do anything,
no matter how bonkers,
just to make you his.
No, that's not it.
I realized it that night.
That man doesn't love me at all.
He was cold.
A completely different person.
It was scary.
A different person, huh?
[ADDICTS groaning]
[SISTINE]
Professor?
[GLENN]
Terminal addicts?
[GLENN] But why is Angel's Dust
starting to show up again now?
Uh... this is bad, isn't it?
[ADDICTS groaning]
--Get back.
--Everyone, back!
Now.
[ADDICTS groaning, growling]
Sorry we're late.
Re=L, keep everyone safe.
Leave this to us.
--Go, now!
--[WENDY] Okay!
[CECIL]
Don't have to tell me twice!
Are you coming?
All right, let's go!
Okay!
Well, men?
Let's do this.
Right!
[ADDICTS groaning]
Don't move!
Damn it!
They got us trapped.
But why?
What's wrong with these people?
[GLENN] At this point,
they're basically just
dead flesh-puppets,
blindly following
their master's orders.
But never mind that. Go!
Just get outta here!
I can't deal with these
burnouts and babysit you
at the same time!
Oh, don't you worry about me!
I can take care of myself,
thank you very much!
Pay heed, great wind...
[GLENN]
Rush forth, wind!
Rush and blow through...
[ADDICT 12B yelling]
[GLENN]
...piercing them!
White cat!
Don't just stand
there lookin' pretty!
Let's go!
[ADDICTS growling]
[GLENN]
Thunder sprites...
[ADDICT 12A yelps]
[SISTINE gasps]
[GLENN] ...pay heed and strike
with your... electric shock!
[ADDICT 12G choking]
No!
[GLENN]
Hey, get a grip!
This way!
[ADDICTS groaning]
[GLENN]
Damn it!
I can't help but think we're
just being herded by Leos.
Is he trying to
ensnare white cat?
Like they did with her?
[GLENN]
Sara!
You bastards!
[GLENN]
That's it!
That's what this is about!
That son of a bitch!
I can't let him do it!
If I half-ass it this time,
I'll lose her again.
Remember, you were an
Imperial Court Mage, damn it!
[ADDICTS yelling]
[SISTINE]
I'm.. so scared...
White cat! Behind you!
Son of a... !
[SISTINE gasps]
[GLENN]
White cat, are you all right?
Get away from me!
[GLENN] You're afraid
of me now, aren't you?
[GLENN]
Sorry.
[SISTINE]
Just... give me a minute.
[clapping]
[LEOS]
Bravo. [laughs]
Jolly good show, Glenn.
Bastard!
You can drop the Leos disguise!
Well done.
I thought you might figure
out my true identity
sooner or later.
That man isn't Leos.
He's former Imperial
Court Mage Corps
Executioner Number Eleven,
Justice, Jatice Lowfan.
You look surprised.
Didn't think I was
still alive, did ya?
Wait. Where is Leos?
Tell me!
Oh, that pompous little turd?
I gave him my drug so
he would do my bidding,
but the weakling had
to go and die on me.
What a drag.
If I'm being honest,
he was pretty much
a dead man already
once I gave him
the Angel's Dust.
That was right after the
Mage Corps Battle ended,
if I'm not mistaken.
[SISTINE]
No...
It's been a while,
hasn't it, Glenn?
You have no idea
how long I've waited,
eagerly wanting to
spar with you again.
White cat, get away from here.
Huh?
This isn't a world you
should be any part of.
I agree, now go and
make yourself scarce.
Your role in this
production has reached
its conclusion.
If you attempt to
interfere in my battle
with Glenn... I'll kill you.
[SISTINE gasps]
[GLENN]
You heard him.
Go!
Take care now.
[JATICE]
You know, she really does bear
an uncanny resemblance to Sara.
[GLENN]
Shut the hell up!
So you established
contact with Leos,
arranged our duel,
and even planned a damn
wedding, all for what?
To orchestrate this battle
between me and you?
[JATICE chuckles]
That's right.
[GLENN] Well, guess I fell
for your original magic,
with its ability to predict
how events will play out.
So, what's your goal here?
Precisely the same
as it was a year ago.
To exact justice.
You just use
justice as an excuse,
so you can go around murdering
all the powerful mages
of the army,
not to mention important
figures in the empire!
[JATICE]
That about sums it up.
Though you left out
the part where you
interrupted me midway through.
But this time, all will
go according to plan
once I obtain the
Akashic Records!
Akashic Records?
[JATICE]
Yes.
Containing the power
to rule over
the very principles
of this world!
And I will have
it all to myself!
But its power can
only be held by one
who is absolutely just.
And therefore,
I shall have no right
to posses it until
I've defeated you,
who thwarted my justice.
Even if it were allowed somehow,
I would never abide
such a thing!
This is not my
revenge against you!
No, it is my challenge to you!
I will be a mage of justice,
and as such,
render judgment upon
all the evil in this world!
[GLENN] As if that kinda
justice actually exists!
I should've known it was you
as soon as you pulled out
those tulpas the other night!
[SISTINE] All this time,
I thought that Professor Radars
didn't belong in our world.
So I rejected him.
But, over and over again,
the professor has risked
his life to protect ours.
I've been a fool.
I've pushed him away.
[crying]
At this point, he's probably
going to leave us
and go somewhere far away,
but what can I do about
it in my condition?
What should I do?
[JATICE]
No use hiding from me, Glenn.
I'm just getting
started here!
[GLENN] Great rule of time,
balance of the scales.
Let the plate of
order tip portside.
Silver ice wolf,
race forth, clad in blizzard!
How you like this?
[JATICE laughs]
You're as resourceful as ever.
Yes, now that's
what I want to see!
Shut up!
I can barely hear
myself killing you!
[GLENN grunts]
[JATICE]
Ah, it seems I've won,
but don't worry, Glenn,
as a sign of merciful
respect I promise
to make your death as quick
and painless as possible.
Please do give
my regards to Sara
in the other world.
[SISTINE]
I made it in time.
[GLENN]
White cat! You...
You moron!
Why'd you come back?
I told you, you don't
belong in this world!
[SISTINE] That's right, and
you don't belong in it either.
I came for a reason.
To bring you back!
Remember you told me
if I want to protect her
that I'd have to be stronger.
Well, Rumia is
irreplaceable to me,
but now, so are you!
[SISTINE] When you're scary
and when you're being a loser.
They're both part
of who you are,
and nobody could
ever replace you!
So stay!
Stay by our sides
and keep fighting!
Don't you dare leave us!
[JATICE]
My goodness.
You certainly caught
me off guard there.
[SISTINE] Listen, just leave
Professor Radars alone!
[JATICE]
My, you're a pest.
Even your personality
resembles that brat Sara's.
Ain't that a bitch.
I must be losing my edge.
Don't need this
straightjacket anymore.
Hey, white cat, two-man cell.
I'll be in front,
you take the rear.
Got it?
[GLENN]
Here's the deal.
I will destroy this jerk, even
if it means going down with him,
but no matter what,
I'll make sure you get
outta this in one piece.
So just...
[SISTINE] Sorry, but I
don't accept those terms.
Now, if you agree that we'll
both make it home safely,
then you've got yourself a deal,
all right, Professor?
I guess I can do that.
Thanks, Sistine.
Well, I'm shocked.
So you do know my
real name after all.
Today's full of surprises.
Go time!
[JATICE] What a nuisance
you are... Sistine Fibel!
Enough of your meddling!
[SISTINE]
Gather round, storm,
become scattered shells,
and fire through!
I warned you not
to interfere in my fight
with Glenn!
[SISTINE] Wall of great
wind, form twofold,
and protect us!
An immediate alteration?
Wind wolf blowing
down the mountains,
race forth quick and violent,
with us at your... back!
[GLENN yelling]
[JATICE growls]
Curse her!
I didn't expect the
girl to be so skilled.
A grave miscalculation
on my part.
O, come!
The manifestation of justice,
sleeping in my depths!
The god who belongs to me!
The god of justice!
Eliminate those villains
who bare their fangs
against my justice!
Lady Justice, Justia!
[laughing]
[SISTINE]
Pay heed, great breath!
[JATICE]
What... have you done?!
Call! Call! Call!
You're done, goocher!
[GLENN yelling]
Let's finish this.
[JATICE laughing]
Don't get cocky, Glenn.
It was two against one,
you needed her.
But what a pity,
she can't help you now.
Mana deficiency.
Guess she's reached her limit.
[JATICE]
Still, in honor of her efforts,
I can be a good sport
and admit defeat for today.
[GLENN]
You all right?
[JATICE] You may not
realize it yet, Glenn...
...but this empire
needs to be destroyed.
Because the awful truth is
this entire nation was
founded with the evilest
of intentions.
May we meet again soon, Glenn.
Next time, my justice will
surely triumph over you.
[GLENN]
Oh stuff it!
And never show your face
here again, you creep!
[GLENN]
Can you stand?
I don't think
I can move at all.
[GLENN grunts]
[RUMIA]
Sisti!
Thank goodness!
Glenn, you're alive!
We were worried about you!
Professor!
Are you guys hurt?
Do you need help?
You guys look great!
[GROUP chattering]
Hey, you sure you're comfortable
having a degenerate
like me as your teacher?
Don't be stupid.
The fact that I'm
still here by your side
right now should be all
the answer that you need.
Don't you think, Professor?
[GLENN] Sorry I let Jatice
just slip away like that.
No need to apologize.
Especially since I didn't
ask you to help us with that.
That psycho.
Still spewing
all kinds of crazy,
messed-up nonsense...
But there was one thing
that perked my ears.
[JATICE] The Akashic
Records contain the power
to rule over the very
principles of this world!
And I will soon have
it all to myself!
[GLENN] Seemed like
he was pretty desperate
to get his hands on that.
[ALBERT]
The Akashic Records, huh?
Interesting.
[ELEANOR]
So deep in here.
Is the door to be opened?
[laughing]
Morning, starshine!
Nice weather we're havin',
eh, Professor Halloween?
It's pronounced "Halley"!
You're doing that on
purpose now, aren't you?
Later, Professor Halitosis.
Halley! Halley Astry!
I'll have you know, sir,
halitosis is a serious
medical condition
with a painful stigma...
Celica! You're back!
Well, you're looking
more like a real teacher
these days.
Told ya, didn't I?
Would be a breeze
if I just tried a little.
[CELICA]
Good.
Then I don't have to
worry about you anymore.
I'm thinking of heading
out on an exploration
of the underground labyrinth.
I haven't been able
to shake the feeling
that there's some important work
that I need to be
doing down there.
[GLENN]
I see.
[SISTINE]
Professor!
Hurry up, you're gonna be late!
I'm counting on you, Professor!
[GLENN]
You're a real pain in the ass.
[GLENN (CHILD)]
"And the Demon Lord asked,
'What are you?
What drives you to such lengths?
How are you capable of all this?
I can't fathom why you'd risk,
and endure, so much.'
Without hesitation
the mage answered,
[GLENN]
'That's simple, Demon Lord.
There are things
I wish to protect.
Things I must protect.
It is this conviction, and
understanding of my duties,
that causes infinite
power to spring
from my depths.
And lets me rise again.'"
Yep, I rise again.
[GLENN]
Hello, kiddoes.
Settle in.
'Cause class is in session!
[ALL]
Yes, sir!