That was a close one.
Are you okay?
Yes, thank you, Professor.
But...
Hey! I know.
You don't have to tell me.
Teaching's the last
thing a guy like me
should be doing.
These hands are
just too damn dirty!
[SISTINE] Professor Radars,
that's not what I mean.
Um...
Your pants fell down!
[GLENN gasps]
How did that happen?!
[GLENN] So the other
mage kidnapped Rumia?
--[SISTINE] Yeah.
--[GLENN] Why target her?
[SISTINE]
Um, no idea.
Looks like we'll have to
get it out of this one.
[beeping noise]
What the hell, Celica?
Don't you answer your calls?
I've been trying to reach
you for the last hour!
[CELICA]
Sorry.
I was in the middle
of a big speech.
Is something up?
Don't mess with me, Glenn.
I wouldn't joke about
this kinda thing!
Some seriously nasty
mages have come in here
and completely sealed
off the Academy!
They've taken most
of the students hostage.
[CELICA] Do you know
what group they're with?
[GLENN]
Yeah.
Researchers of Divine Wisdom.
[CELICA gasps]
I see. The top of the
evil mage food chain.
Why are the worst terrorists
in the Empire's history
interested in our school?
All I know right now
is they shouldn't have
broken through the magic
security as easily as they did.
That means...
[CELICA] They must have
an inside man at the school.
Bingo.
Can you dig around on your end
and see if you turn up
any suspicious professors?
And while you're at it,
ask the Court Mage Corps for--
Glenn, that won't be easy.
Make it easy!
There are students'
lives at stake here!
Calm down.
[CELICA] Right now,
I'm just a professor, like you.
I lack the authority.
Fine! Then you get
back here and help!
You can use the
teleportation circle!
Waste of time.
If these Divine Wisdom guys
were able to seize our barrier,
I'm assuming they also destroyed
the teleportation circle.
Good point.
I'm shooting from the hip here.
[CELICA]
But don't worry.
I'll do what I can to get there.
[GLENN]
Please do.
Hey, Glenn?
[GLENN]
What?
Stay alive.
Thanks!
What a great idea, Doctor!
What's wrong?
[SISTINE]
We're not getting help, are we?
[GLENN]
Probably not, punchy.
What are you doing?
I'm going to get Rumia!
Oh, please.
They'll destroy you!
[SISTINE]
Shut up!
I don't know how to help.
Hey. Stop.
Don't cry here.
You were right
before, Professor.
Magic isn't good for anything!
It's 'cause of magic
that Rumia...
That she...
[GLENN]
Don't cry, white cat.
Thank you.
Rumia told me her life's goal
is to understand magic better.
Make it more useful
for normal folks.
It's a nice thought.
Seriously?
She told you that?
She's not gonna die.
I'll save her.
I'll find the other
two evil mages.
And kill them.
[JIN laughing]
Kill them, huh?
Well, that's weird.
You're a hell of a lot more
like us than I expected.
No! Professor Radars is
nothing like you people!
Oh, no, no.
I read him like a book.
Your prof's got "bastard"
written all over him.
Go on!
Admit you're no
different from us!
Um... What now?
[SISTINE gasps]
Professor?
[GLENN]
Bone golems!
[JIN]
Reinforcements!
Our boss's summoning magic!
Thank you, leader!
[BONE GOLEMS growling]
No, wait...
They're the enemy.
Get them.
Somebody help me!
[SISTINE screams]
Stay behind me!
[yelling]
[GLENN gasps]
Aww, cripes!
And they say I'm the one
who's hard headed around here!
Upon thy sword, light!
Nice one. Eat this, bonehead!
[yelling]
--Let's go!
--Uh, right!
I'll hold 'em back!
While I do that, can you
alter your Gale Blow spell
so it reaches maximum
range and duration?
Uh, no?
That's really advanced!
[GLENN] Please.
I know you can do this.
It's not that hard.
Don't be so... stubborn.
I'm not stubborn, I'm honest!
[GLENN] I guarantee if
you've listened to even half
of what I've been teaching,
you can do this,
no problem.
And if you can't,
I'll dock your grade.
You son of a bitch!
All right, then.
Here goes nothing.
Don't let me down, white cat.
[GLENN]
C'mon, you calcified corpses!
[BONE GOLEMS growl]
[SISTINE] Wind, be still,
but then, the force.
Tempest, run rampant,
but so that you
may last longer.
How do I do this?
This spell needs the
same strength Rumia showed
in the classroom.
[SISTINE] And the strength
of the professor,
who's risking his life while
he trusts me to get this done!
It's my turn to save him!
It's ready! I got it!
Nice work.
Now let 'em have it!
Keep them all at bay.
Wall of tempest.
Grant peace to them below!
Oh, no!
I can't stop them completely!
Sorry, Professor!
[GLENN]
Don't be sorry.
You did great.
Keep it up.
I'm he who slays
and captures gods!
I am the one who knows the end
and the founder of genesis!
Now return thyself to
the cycle of providence.
The five elements to elements,
and sever the link woven
between images and the truth!
I declare that all creation
shall perish here--
at the distant ends of the void!
Prepare to be blasted, rabble!
Black magic!
Extinction Ray!
[BONE GOLEMS growling]
Oh, wow.
I've never seen such
a high level spell.
[GLENN groans]
[SISTINE]
Professor!
You're freezing!
Your mana must be low.
That's what happens
when you force yourself
to do a spell beyond your means.
We've gotta get
out of here, right now!
Doesn't matter where.
[footsteps]
Too late.
They're not about to back down.
[REIK]
I'm impressed that you know how
to use an Extinction Ray.
I heard you were nothing more
but a low-rent mage.
I underestimated you.
[GLENN]
Wow, really?
I think somebody might
be overcompensating
with his flying swords.
I didn't think you'd beat
both Jin and Carrell.
Screw you.
Your Bone Golems
killed one of them.
Don't blame me for that.
Hey, white cat.
Do you think you
have enough power left
to clear out those swords
with a Dispel Force?
Sorry, but I don't think even
using all my remaining power
will be enough.
Besides, there's
no opening for it.
Okay.
Well, then.
Bye.
[SISTINE]
What?
Uh...
Hey!
[crash]
Here we go.
[REIK]
I would run if I were you.
I know your "Fool's World."
How you can use it
to prevent spells
from going into effect.
Too bad it can't stop spells
that are already active.
[GLENN yells]
Stupid magic swords!
[GLENN] But no matter
how dangerous he is,
his mana fluctuates before
and after using magic.
Maybe I can time it
for just that moment.
Crimson Lion!
Pay heed and roar with--
Dispel Force.
You're far too slow, Professor.
Allow me to teach you.
Flame Lion.
[GLENN]
Got you!
Thunder emperor!
[REIK]
What?
[GLENN] Pierce with
your brilliant lance...
...of light!
[GLENN] Damn, I thought
for sure I'd connect
with at least one.
[REIK] It seems you're
trying to force me
to choose between
two deaths, Professor.
Had I continued with Flame Lion,
you would have sealed it
and then attacked me
in hand-to-hand combat.
If I chose to use the swords,
you would have capitalized
on my fluctuation in mana
to hit me with
a Lightning Pierce.
Tell me.
Just who are you?
I'm just a magic teacher.
Well, a substitute.
That's a lie.
But I will show
you some respect.
Now die!
Creation, pay heed...
[REIK]
Dispel Force?
[GLENN grunts]
...maintain the balance
of the scales.
Too late for that.
Re... turn!
I'm sorry.
You don't have the power.
You're done!
[SISTINE]
Return them to nothing!
What?
Professor!
[GLENN yelling]
[REIK]
Awaken Blade--
Too slow!
I... I remember.
Till recently, there was a
deadly mage killer in the--
in the Imperial Court Mages.
His codename was...
[GLENN] Wish it didn't
have to be so gruesome.
You hurt?
No, I'm good.
I'm just...
I'm surprised you got my intent.
Huh?
Hey!
He's trying to get rid of me?
That jerk!
[crash]
Maybe I am useless
in this fight.
Do you think you
have enough power left
to clear out those swords
with a Dispel Force?
If you were really
trying to get rid of me,
you wouldn't have asked
about my power levels first.
[chuckles]
I thought there was a 70%
chance you wouldn't get it.
Well... Let's roll.
Wait...
You better not fight
anymore in that condition.
It's not like I have
a choice, Sistine!
[grunting]
[SISTINE]
Professor!
[GLENN]
Damn, it hurts.
Merciful angels, pay heed,
and grant him your peace.
Your saving grace.
I guess... it's not my fate.
[SISTINE]
What?
I had always wanted
to be a Mage of Justice.
[beeping noise]
[CELICA]
Glenn! You're alive!
[GLENN]
Yeah, somehow. How are you?
[CELICA]
Eh.
Just like I thought, they shut
down the teleportation circles.
No luck finding the
collaborator, either.
But Glenn, those aren't
the biggest problems.
[GLENN]
Huh?
[CELICA] It looks like the
barrier around the Academy
has been set to keep people in.
So they're criminals
who don't plan
on getting away with it?
[GLENN] I'm guessing
they haven't attacked
since I killed Reik.
But with the barrier,
they're still here.
What the hell are they doing?
Celica.
Tell me where the
transportation circle is.
[CELICA] At the very top
room of the tallest tower.
But what's the point?
The teleportation
circle isn't shut down.
They're rewriting
its destination
so they can make their escape.
[CELICA]
That's nuts.
It'd take half a day to do that!
That's right.
Which means they should
be just about done with it.
[GLENN]
Ow! Dammit.
[sighs]
Still in one piece, though.
I owe you big, Sistine.
I was lucky to have you
in my corner today.
And with that,
I'm off to save Rumia!
[RUMIA]
Why are you doing this?
You were an educator,
not a terrorist!
[GLENN yelling]
You're here!
[GLENN]
Rumia!
Um, are you all right?
Well I look worse than I feel,
and I still feel pretty bad.
[footsteps]
So you're the big boss, huh?
[HUEY]
Indeed, I am, professor.
Good gravy, who invited
Mr. Pretty Pants?
Aren't you late for
a hair appointment?
Anyway, I've had a long day,
so I've got no patience left
no matter how shiny
your face might be!
First strike wins.
Got that?
You should, 'cause I nailed it.
So why don't you give--
No, I win.
What does that mean?!
[HUEY] In ten minutes,
we'll have finished rewriting
the circle's
destination coordinates.
Rumia will be transported
directly to our base.
Then, the white magic
ritual I just finished
will activate.
This Sacrifice spell
will devour my soul,
releasing an incredible
amount of mana.
Enough energy, in fact,
to blow up the school.
[GLENN gasps]
[RUMIA]
No!
Don't do it, Professor Huey!
Huey?
So this is the professor
who left that I replaced?
You're the inside man!
I prefer to see myself
as a human bomb,
ticking down for years,
and finally ready to explode.
Well, thanks for reminding me.
You Researchers of Divine
Wisdom aren't just evil,
you're total nut jobs.
You can still win this game.
[GLENN]
Huh?
[HUEY] If you can counter
the Teleportation Circle
binding Rumia,
then Sacrifice won't activate.
But if you simply wait for
the Fool's World to run out,
you won't be able to dispel
it with the time lost.
So, Glenn,
will you play the game?
[RUMIA]
Don't worry about me, Professor!
Get out of here
and save yourself!
I'm afraid it's no use
attacking me with magic
or your fists.
If I die, then all of this
activates automatically.
[GLENN]
Power of creation, pay heed,
and pass through my
blood to form your path!
Using your own
blood as a catalyst.
That's impressive.
[GLENN]
Let the divine cycle end.
Let the foundation of calm,
the yoke of principles,
be unleashed in this spot!
Well done.
However...
That was only the first of
five layers you must undo.
Dammit!
Professor Radars,
don't worry about me.
Just go!
[GLENN]
Shut up! I'm working!
Professor, please stop
doing these spells!
They're going to kill you!
Oh, yeah.
I bet the white cat would
get a real kick out of that!
[RUMIA]
Please stop.
You don't have to
do this for me.
I don't want you
risking your life!
[GLENN]
Y'know...
I always wanted to be
a mage of justice.
But it was just my luck
that the world of magic
is actually a filthy,
blood-stained place.
Bummer.
I've nearly wasted
my whole damn life.
And yet, I'm not about
to give up on it, either!
[GLENN] If I'm someone
who runs away from trouble,
then what was the
purpose of any of this?
Those years I spent trying
to be a mage of justice.
I know they were a failure.
But...
I won't let them be worthless!
You got a problem
with that, buddy?
Do you see that?
One more to go.
[retching]
[coughs]
No, don't!
Almost... there.
I got the worst luck.
Can't believe I ran out of mana.
Damn.
I tried.
Professor!
I made it!
Since you didn't give up,
I won't, either!
You hear me?
Here.
This is for you, Professor.
[GLENN]
What is this power?
I've heard of this before.
People with the ability
to dramatically increase
the power of those they touch.
They're called amplifiers.
[yelling]
Let the divine cycle end!
Foundation of calm.
Yoke of principles,
be unleashed!
It appears that I lost.
Oh, well.
Should I have died following
the Researchers' orders?
Or should I have died
ignoring them?
Since you won the day,
maybe you have the answer.
[GLENN]
Yeah, I don't care.
Look, I'm sorry
it's over for you,
but it's your own fault for
not choosing a better path.
And now I'm gonna do something
about that shiny face.
[GLENN] Show me them
pearly whites, Pretty Pants.
[SISTINE panting]
Is he--?
[RUMIA]
Shh!
Thank you, Professor.
So Rumia used to be
Princess Ermiana.
Then three years back,
she fakes her own death.
Yeah, because society
persecutes those with powers.
People would revolt if
they knew a royal had 'em.
Only two people
at the Academy know.
Me and the Headmaster.
Well... I don't really care.
Is that so?
Then what made you decide
to keep teaching here?
[SISTINE]
Hey, there he is!
[RUMIA]
Professor Radars!
I have serious questions
for you after that last lecture.
I decided to stay
here because, well,
I want to see what they're
capable of achieving.
And it's a good place to nap.