♪
[ITSUKI] In my second year
of middle school,
my mother passed away.
Then, in my second year
of high school,
my father remarried.
It had only been three years,
but he already found
someone new.
I resented him for that.
I still haven’t patched things
up with my father.
[CHIHIRO humming]
But, my relationship
with my new little brother
is going pretty well.
Something wrong?
Nothing.
Just thinking.
♪
-Hey, guess what.
-Hmm?
I’m about to start
a part-time job!
Oh, cool. What kind?
I’ll be helping out that tax
accountant, Ashley Ono.
-[ITSUKI coughing]
-Whoa. Are you okay?
[ITSUKI]
Yeah, I'm fine.
Something just went down
the wrong pipe.
But forget about me,
why the hell would you want
to work for her of all people?
I don’t know, she’s was just
the one to offer.
She said that I’d be cleaning
and organizing files.
So it’s no different
from what I usually do here.
On top of that,
she also agreed to help me
study accounting.
So what?
Now you want to be
an accountant too?
[CHIHIRO] That’s not exactly
what I had in mind.
I just thought I could pick up
a few things and help you out.
[groans] You already help me out
so much as it is.
I wouldn’t want to put you
through all that.
Don’t worry about it.
This is something I want to do.
Okay. Just do me a favor
and be careful.
[CHIHIRO]
Sure.
This is the place, right?
[elevator whirring]
♪
[CHIHIRO gasps]
Pardon the intrusion.
This is an accounting office.
Isn’t it?
[ASHLEY giggles]
[gasps]
Glad you could make it, Chihiro.
[CHIHIRO] Hello!
I look forward to
working with you.
[ASHLEY giggles]
Believe me,
the pleasure’s all mine.
Right.
I can’t help but notice
it’s just the two of us.
Very observant.
This is my busiest time of year
so I need extra help.
But otherwise,
it’s just myself here.
Well that makes sense.
[ASHLEY giggles]
Calm your nerves, boy.
I won’t gobble you up.
[chuckles]
Um, so is there something
lined up for me to do?
There is.
I’d like you to do a little
cleaning in the back.
[CHIHIRO]
As in through that door?
Yes, this is also my residence.
So I’ve got my bedroom
and kitchen back there.
Oh, interesting.
[CHIHIRO gasps, groans]
I manage to keep
the office clean,
so I can keep a professional
image in front of customers.
But I can never find the time
to tidy up in here.
[CHIHIRO] I think this goes
beyond "not finding the time."
But, when my big brother first
started living on his own,
his place was like this, too.
[CHIHIRO]
Ms. Ono?
What is it?
Question.
Would you mind
if I gave this my all?
Uh, that’s fine.
Go right ahead.
-[chittering]
-[gasps]
[yells]
-[chittering]
-[gasps]
[yells]
-[chittering]
-[gasps]
[yells]
[chittering]
[squish]
[chuckles]
It’s like a completely
different room.
I didn’t expect you
to clean this thoroughly.
Well, it’s been a while
since I really got to clean,
so it was kinda fun.
You did well.
I set up the bath for you.
Use it, if you’d like.
I know you worked up a sweat.
I did.
You know what?
Why not?
I’ll take you up on that offer.
Chihiro, just so you know,
the towels are--.
What?
[CHIHIRO whimpers]
[ASHLEY]
So, you’re a girl.
Considering my line of work,
it’s a given that I’ll meet
a lot of interesting people.
But for those I’ve met so far,
you take the cake.
[CHIHIRO]
The only person in my family
who thinks I’m a boy
is my brother.
I even go to school as a girl,
and no bats an eye.
I just pretend
to be Itsuki’s brother
to his editor and friends.
And by chance,
now I’ve found out.
[giggles]
Please. Don’t tell him.
Hmm.
I am in a predicament.
Please, don’t!
You can relax, I’m only kidding.
Don’t worry I’m not into
bullying girls
with smaller boobs than mine.
Thank you,
I really appreciate it.
[ASHLEY]
But even so.
This isn’t a secret that you’ll
be able to keep forever.
Trust me, I know.
I plan to tell my brother
the truth someday,
I just don’t know when.
You have to wonder how he’ll
react when the time comes.
Given his love
for little sisters,
when he finds out
he actually has one,
who knows what he’ll do.
Oh my.
How intriguing.
[ASHLEY giggles]
[roaring]
[PROTAGONIST] When I woke up,
my naked little sister
was letting out
a nightmarish roar
as she spewed
her vile mucus everywhere.
G’morning, sis.
[MONSTER roaring]
You’re as cute as ever.
[MONSTER roars]
[PROTAGONIST]
My little sister stands
just under two meters tall.
But when she’s intimidating
an enemy,
she swells up
to about five meters.
Her body is covered
in protrusions.
She has fifteen bumps
on her shoulders and back,
and every once in a while,
I can see something resembling
a brain floating inside.
For the most part,
she sees humans as food.
So it can be a bit
of a challenge
to communicate with her.
Hey wait, you tried to eat me
again last night, didn’t you?
Bad girl.
[MONSTER roars]
[PROTAGONIST] I can tell
by the look on her... self
that she’s sorry.
How cute.
[roaring]
[squelching, thudding]
[TOKI growls]
[groans]
[TOKI]
Explain.
It’s a draft for my new project.
I wrote it to explore a new
concept I was thinkin’ about.
Which is?
Could you possibly love
a grotesque abomination
just because it was
your little sister?
I guess you could consider
that the theme.
Interesting.
So, could you?
[ITSUKI]
Could I what?
Could you, as the author,
bring yourself to love this
creature from another dimension
that only sees you as food?
Because it’s a little sister?
Just barely, but yeah.
If you don’t even like it,
how the hell do you expect
normal readers to?
[sighs]
I’m okay with you working
on a new project,
but you better be progressing
with volume six
of Mahou Academy.
[scoffs] Have no fear.
I just have to finish up the
climax and then I’ll be done.
[TOKI]
Fail to meet your deadline again
and you’re headed
straight back to that prison.
I’m actually fine this time,
I’ll get it done.
[keyboard clacking]
[sighs]
[ITSUKI sighs]
Hey, Kanikou.
You wanna go to the zoo?
[NAYUTA] Huh? You mean
it’ll be just the two of us?
Just calm down.
It’s for research, I just
thought you might want to--
I’m in!
[indistinct chatter]
Well, it’s a lot less crowded
than the amusement park was.
Yeah, I guess it’s always best
to go out on the weekdays.
You said it!
But oh man, it’s been so long
since I’ve been to the zoo!
[ITSUKI] I haven’t been here
since I came
with my family as a kid.
All right, Itsuki!
You ready to go
voyeuristically leer
at these naked beasts
locked up in cages?
Why do you have to make
a zoo visit gross?
[NAYUTA] Oh!
Check him out, he’s huge!
[ITSUKI]
Yeah, look at that thing.
[CHILD]
The panda’s so cute, Mom!
[MOM]
Yes, it’s adorable!
[gasps]
He’s got his third leg
out on display
for all these people.
If he were human, he’d be
arrested for indecent exposure.
You’re right.
Not exactly a role model
for the cubs.
[NAYUTA]
You know what I just realized?
Pandas are kind of
like old men.
[ITSUKI chuckling]
Yeah.
I could imagine that thing
yellin’ at me
to get off his lawn.
[NAYUTA]
Oh, check it out.
It says here that this panda is
about thirty in human years.
[ITSUKI] You’re at the prime
of your career.
Get it together, man!
What are you doing?
Well, when you think about it,
he kind of is working.
It’s just that his job
is to slack off
and be an exhibitionist.
Apparently, he rests in his
own room when the zoo is closed.
And he’s got heated floors
and a private pool in there.
Sounds like a sweet deal.
Somehow, he’s the most popular
animal at the zoo,
despite doing nothing.
Well, if his presence alone
is enough to get people here,
of course they’re gonna
take care of him.
He’s like an animal celebrity.
If that was you
naked in there, Itsuki,
I’d come watch you
all day long, too!
Come on, let’s go
see the next one.
[CHILD]
He’s so funny!
Panda!
Hey, Panda!
[CHILD giggling]
♪
[indistinct chatter]
This turned into
a normal zoo trip.
Even though I came here to get
some ideas on the monster
I’m putting in
my final battle.
Hmm? Somethin’ up?
I was just thinking about
the nads on that kangaroo
we saw before.
What about ’em?
I just can’t stop
thinking about it.
They were just dangling
from his crotch,
swaying back and forth.
[ITSUKI]
Yeah, they were.
If he used those
powerful legs to jump,
wouldn’t the momentum rip
them off and send them flying?
That’s a terrifying thought.
I know, but just
imagine it.
Kangaroos are known
for kickboxing.
Someone should invent a cup
for those poor guys.
And I don’t know if you noticed,
but the lions and elephants were
showin’ off their goods, too.
I took a bunch of pictures.
[ITSUKI]
Well, this is awful.
Now I just need to snap
a picture of a human’s,
and my collection
will be complete.
[NAYUTA giggles]
Why ya looking me?
Don’t look at my crotch either!
[laughs]
I already have a naked
picture of you,
would it really be
all that different?
[ITSUKI screams]
You took a picture?
Delete that!
Come on!
No way!
This is my pride and joy.
[giggling]
Oh Itsuki and your cute,
defenseless little rear end.
[NAYUTA kissing]
[SIEG]
Chrom!
So you were the one behind this,
after all!
[CHROM chuckles]
Are you enjoying your stay
in my amusement park from hell?
Return us to our world now,
or you’ll be sorry!
[CHROM snickers]
Don’t be in such a hurry.
You haven’t even witnessed
my brilliant plan yet.
[SIEG]
What?
Arise, my minions
of pure darkness!
[CHROM yelling]
[heavy thudding]
Get your ass off my lawn
or we’re gonna have a problem.
[ITSUKI] Maybe I’m forcing
the old man parallel here.
[ITSUKI sighs]
A lion?
Alligator?
I already made an enemy out
of a carnivore before,
I don’t wanna do it again.
Maybe I just gotta start
thinkin’ outside the box here.
Yeah. I’m goin’ out for a bit.
Where to?
[ITSUKI]
The aquarium.
I was so distracted
by the whale shark in Okinawa
that I wasn’t even paying
attention to the other fish.
The aquarium?
Sounds fun.
You can tag along if you want.
Really? Let’s go!
[gasp]
I think this is the first time
just the two of us
have ever gone
to do something.
Now that you mention it,
I guess it is.
[ITSUKI]
After my father remarried...
I did everything I could
to avoid interacting
with my new family.
I’m not sure if Chihiro was
trying to respect my privacy,
but he kept his distance.
Our relationship only gained
some traction
after I started
living on my own.
And now, I think we’re
getting along just as well
as any normal,
blood-related brothers could.
To think it’s already been
about four years.
Time sure does fly.
Hmm?
Are you all right?
Your face is red.
Yeah. I’m fine.
It’s just a little tight
in here.
♪
Wow, this is amazing!
[ITSUKI]
Wow!
Hey, look at that!
Those are sardines!
That’s what I cooked for you
the other day, remember?
[ITSUKI]
Uh, yeah.
They were pretty good.
And would you check out
that tuna?
That would make a big meal!
Look at that freaking huge
Red Snapper!
Oh, and there’s a shark!
I gotta make you
some muenière sometime!
There are a lot of other ones
I don’t know, too.
I wonder if they taste good.
[ITSUKI] You really just
see them as food, don’t you?
[CHIHIRO giggling]
Wasn’t that fun?
[ITSUKI]
Yeah.
I know you were
hoping to do research.
I hope I didn't get in the way.
Nah, not at all.
Actually, I got a new idea
thanks to you.
Really?
Yeah, a character that sees
everything as food.
Sound familiar?
Hey, I don’t do that!
I just cook with fish
a lot so it’s on my mind!
And I liked those jellyfish
cause they were cute!
But you’d eat them, right?
I mean, yeah, but...
It’s nice to see you get so
excited about the little things.
Well, can you blame me for it?
You rarely take me anywhere,
so I had to make the most of it.
[ITSUKI]
Oh yeah?
What’s up?
Whaddya say we go somewhere
again sometime soon?
-Really?
-Sure.
[laughs softly]
That’d be great!
Then it’s a promise.
[ITSUKI]
Yeah. It’s a promise.
It’s getting late,
so I’m gonna head home.
I’ll come by tomorrow
to cook for you.
[ITSUKI]
Cool.
[TRAIN ANNOUNCER]
We have an announcement to make.
Due to an accident
involving an injury,
the inbound train is currently
suspended from operation.
We will make
another announcement
when the line
is back in service.
We apologize for any
inconvenience this may cause.
Oh, great.
Sounds like it’ll take a while.
Well, I’d rather grab a taxi
than wait around here.
We’re headed in the same
direction anyway,
so you can ride with me
if you want.
So which fish that we saw
was your favorite?
The spotted garden eel.
It moved all funny.
Yeah. I thought that one
was adorable.
With that kind of name,
and the way it wiggled,
I’m pretty sure Kanikou
would have loved it.
[giggling nervously]
Yeah, she would.
Believe it or not, when we went
to the zoo the other day,
she kept taking pictures
of the animals’ dongs.
She’s such a little pervert.
Yeah, she sure is.
Though I have
to wonder about girls
who are that vulgar.
It catches me off guard.
Yeah. I see that.
Gotta say though.
I think it’s cool
that there’s a girl
I can have dirty
conversations with.
[CHIHIRO]
Hmm.
Why don’t you stay
the night tonight?
No one’s touched your room.
It’s just how you left it.
Nah, I’m goin’ home.
Oh, okay.
Well, um,
thanks for taking me home.
[ITSUKI groans]
Oh, Dad.
Chihiro, time for you to go.
Uh, but...
[ITSUKI'S DAD]
Itsuki.
Thanks for the gift.
Really.
[ITSUKI]
Don’t mention it.
The two of you haven’t
spoken in so long.
Hey Dad, don’t you want to talk?
[CHIHIRO]
Guess not.
Well, I’ll see you tomorrow,
right big bro?
[ITSUKI]
Yeah.
[CHIHIRO]
Hey, Itsuki!
Listen.
I really want you and Dad
to patch things up.
We’re family.
[ITSUKI]
We can go now.
I know Chihiro, but...
[sighs]
That was a bad anime
to the very end.
[groans]
Why do people even want
anime adaptations?
Huh?
[HARUTO'S SISTER]
What are you doing?
Havin’ myself a drink.
What’s your excuse
for being up this late?
I don’t have to explain
myself to you.
Okay.
So, uh...
The anime adaption
that you did of your novel,
it just finished airing, right?
You watch?
Not on purpose, I just happened
to turn on the TV.
Oh. Okay.
It was pretty terrible, huh?
Yep. Total trash.
[chuckles] Okay.
[HARUTO'S SISTER]
Worse than trash.
Everyone involved
in making it should die.
Hey now, you don’t have
to get that angry.
Huh? What makes you
think I’m angry?
I refuse to accept
that was your story,
why should I even care?
It was nothing like the book
from episode one.
The animation was so bad,
they weren’t even moving!
The acting was stiff,
the designs looked nothing
like the originals
and the dialogue made no sense
which ruined the story.
Hey I don’t need
your stupid head pats!
Oh, I’m sorry.
I promise.
That won't happen again.
I'm gonna do better next time.
Well, that goes
without saying!
If you let them make garbage
like that again,
I’ll never forgive you.
So work harder on the next one,
okay?
[chuckles softly]
[HARUTO]
I guess I was wrong.
It is nice having a little
sister every now and then.