Oh.
It's you, Miyako.
Whoa, I hardly recognized you!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
I just haven't slept
in a couple of days.
Anyway, you came
at the perfect time.
What?
[ITSUKI]
Could you do me a solid
and deliver this to my editor?
Thanks, you're the best.
-[thud]
-Itsuki?
Like hell you're fine,
you look terrible!
[snoring]
Man.
What am I going to do with you?
Do I just use this
to call him down?
Oh.
May I help you, miss?
Uh, yeah.
I was told to--
Uh, Itsuki Hashima asked me
to deliver something
to Mr. Toki for him.
Okay. Then why don't you
come in.
[YAMAGATA]
Delivery!
Hey, Ken-Ken!
You shut your mouth,
you little-sister obsessed
freak o' nature!
[snoring]
Is everything okay with him?
Happens all the time.
That messy one's his desk,
so why don't you just
leave it there for him?
All right.
[sighs]
[continues snoring]
He must be pushing himself
extra hard.
It's always like this
when proofreading day is near.
Really? Hmm.
Hey.
Isn't that...?
It's the cover for
Nayuta Kani's new volume.
Supposed to go
on sale this month,
but the manuscript
hasn't been turned in yet.
[MIYAKO]
Well, that's no good.
You can say that again.
And I haven't been able
to get a hold of her.
[sighs]
[MIYAKO]
Um...
If you'd like,
I could check up on her.
[YAMAGATA]
What?
Yeah, I can go see her now.
Sorry.
But who are you?
Come on in, Myaa!
Now don't be shy,
take off your clothes!
[MIYAKO]
Uh... 'Kay?
Hold on, I am not here
to mess around, girl!
Aw, that's a shame.
Nayu, I heard you haven't
turned in your manuscript yet.
[squeals]
[MIYAKO]
I saw your editor and she said
she'd been up all night
waiting for it.
How much longer
do you think it'll take?
Um, I dunno.
I'm almost done with the amount
I'm supposed to write.
But I just haven't been able
to keep myself
in the zone lately.
[MIYAKO]
In the zone?
We should totally have some fun!
I just know that I'll feel
more motivated
to get my work done
if you play with me.
No way.
Aww.
Hey. Don't be like that.
We can hang out and do
whatever you want
when your work's done.
I guess you leave me no choice.
But I have one condition.
Let me use your lap as a pillow!
It'll recharge my batteries!
You're like my power cable.
I don't even know
what that means.
But if you really think
it'll help
then I can deal with it.
C'mon.
[laughs]
Wait, you write it
on your phone?
Yeah, sometimes.
I just use whatever I feel
like at the time.
I'll use my laptop,
a stand-alone word processor,
or even paper and pencil.
Well that's convenient.
If you have to be naked,
I guess you're stuck
in this room
no matter what you use.
Yeah.
But laying on your lap
is a good way to mix it up!
[MIYAKO]
You got me there.
Okay, enough messin' around.
Time to get to work!
[phone whirring]
Wow. You're fast.
Manuscript done and submitted!
Good job.
I'm proud of you, Nayu.
[laughs]
Thanks to you, Myaa.
You should be my editor
from now on.
You're great with motivation.
Why are things not going well
with your real editor?
No, things are fine with her.
Then you should probably
keep her in the loop
on your work.
It's not like talking to her
makes me finish
my manuscripts any faster.
Hey, you don't know
that for sure.
Maybe if you actually discussed
your story with her,
she'd give you
some good ideas.
Hmm.
[giggles]
Nah, that wouldn't happen.
[sighs]
Okay.
Ah. What about the fifth line
on page twenty-one?
[YAMAGATA]
Seriously, you're a lifesaver.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I didn't do
anything special.
But we can release
the book thanks to you.
-[sighs]
-Wait, what's wrong?
Now I have to go apologize
to the printers,
the proofreaders,
and the marketing department.
Not the person who couldn't
make the deadline, but me.
I always get stuck
with this stuff.
[exasperated sigh]
I'm well aware that it's my job.
It's what I do.
I just hate getting
the runaround from a little girl
who just happens to be
our most valuable author.
So, um...
I'm guessing that you two
aren't exactly getting along
at the moment?
-We get along.
-[TOKI talking on phone]
But the two of us aren't
creating something together
like those guys are.
Understand?
Well, then maybe
you should talk more
about the content
of her stories.
-[YAMAGATA] No.
-[TOKI yelling]
[YAMAGATA] There's virtually
nothing anyone
could contribute
to better her works.
Even though I'm her editor,
I'm basically
just fixing her typos.
It's infuriating, honestly.
If it's so frustrating,
why don't you
just quit being her editor?
It's never crossed my mind
and it never will.
Are you sure?
Never?
Yes, I'm sure,
and I'll tell you why.
If I quit I wouldn't be the
first one to read her novels.
Then you must love her work.
That's nice to hear.
[TOKI]
Wait. Yeah. Okay. Fine.
I hate to admit it,
but you're right.
[TOKI]
Okay. Aaah!
Ah!
Damn it, shut up for a sec!
We're getting nowhere
over the phone like this!
I'm coming to your place
right now!
Stupid kid.
[TOKI growls]
If I had to do what he does,
I'd be angry too.
[HARUTO]
All right.
In celebration
of our dear friends
Itsuki and Nayu
releasing new volumes,
we toast!
[ALL]
Congratulations!
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you, Myaa!
So thank you very much!
Did Miyako help you out?
Um?
Yeah. She got na--
I just hung out
and kept her company.
Okay.
You know, now that I think
about it,
Kaiko thanked you
for helping her too.
What did you do?
It was nothing!
Seriously, don't worry about it.
Now let's drop it
and if you bring it up again,
I'll break your collarbone.
Why so specific?
Now I'm even more curious
what she did.
[ITSUKI sighs]
It's nice to be able
to take my time eating
now that
I'm done working.
Yeah, I try not to eat too much
before a deadline, too.
Don't wanna get tired
and fall asleep.
[NAYUTA]
Same here.
What do you mean?
You never worry about deadlines.
Well, sure I always
finish my work on time,
but I get tired
when I eat too much.
So I can imagine what it's like
to do that the night
before a deadline.
In other words,
you've never done that.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Okay. Now that
we're all relaxed,
what do you say
we play a game?
Yeah. Good idea.
What did you have in mind?
Huh...
How about Once Upon a Time?
[whistle blows]
[HARUTO]
Once Upon a Time is a game
in which all players
are storytellers,
creating a story, together.
Each player has an ending card
that has,
you guessed it, the ending
to their story on it.
They also have
a number of story cards
that are used
to build their plot.
The first player to use up
all of their story cards
and complete the story
with their ending card
is declared the winner.
Now pay attention,
'cause this part's important.
If any idea from one of
your story cards comes up
while another storyteller
is speaking,
you can present your card
and steal the position
of storyteller from them.
Oh, I get it.
So you want it to be your turn,
because that means you can take
the story in a direction
that uses your cards
and ends with your conclusion.
[HARUTO] There's also an
interrupt card that can be used
when a similar type
of story card is presented
letting a player immediately
steal the turn for themselves.
So be prepared for that.
[ALL]
All right. Okay.
You ready?
Let's decide who goes first
with rock-paper-scissors.
Cool.
Looks like I'll be treating you
to a new story
free of charge.
Once upon a time,
there was an older brother
and his ever-faithful
younger sister.
[HARUTO]
Of course you got that one.
Are we sure we shuffled?
This is divine intervention
telling me to make
a sister story.
I don't even need to say this,
since it's implied,
but the little sister
is young and beautiful.
Yes!
That makes me the storyteller!
I didn't expect the first player
to be interrupted so quickly.
[ITSUKI groans]
[HARUTO]
When the storyteller changes,
the player who was interrupted
has to take
a new story card from the pile.
[ITSUKI groans]
The little sister
was very beautiful.
But unfortunately,
someone put a curse on her
and she was turned into
a not-so-beautiful wolf.
Huh?
Why you gotta ruin
the sister like that?
The one who turned
the little sister into a wolf
was a very cute
and completely naked witch.
Her name is Kaniko.
[laughs]
The witch showed herself
and spoke.
She said, "I've always
loved you from afar!
"If you marry me, I'll return
your little sister to normal.
You wouldn't abandon her,
would you?"
Come on!
Then the older brother thought,
"She cares so much about me
"and she's so adorable, too!
She's the perfect woman."
And so, the two
fell madly in love.
Go back home to your
little sister, man!
Hold on.
I think I can use this
interrupt card, right?
[laughs]
And that makes me
the storyteller now.
Let's see.
As promised, the witch
returned the little sister
to her natural form.
As an unforeseen side effect,
the big brother realized
he liked her better
than the witch.
[NAYUTA]
This guy's a cheating jerk.
[ITSUKI]
Yes! Atta boy, Chihiro!
[CHIHIRO]
Then the big brother said,
"Kaniko, let's get a divorce.
I love my little sister
far too much to be with you."
Kaniko and the older brother
got in a huge argument,
but eventually, she understood
how deep their bond
as siblings was,
and let them be.
And so, the two
were able to return
to their once peaceful lives.
And then they, uh...
[HARUTO] If you can't think
of a way to continue the story,
you can pass.
[CHIHIRO]
Okay. Yeah, then I pass.
[HARUTO]
The storyteller position
is now given to the player
on your left.
[NAYUTA]
Yes, that's me!
Though the witch
had withdrawn once, deep down,
she knew she just couldn't
accept these circumstances.
[whimpers]
The longer the witch witnessed
them living happily together
the greater her hatred grew.
Until one day she
put a curse on them both!
Grow, swell, rise!
Your monster
will stretch sky high!
The witch's magic made
the big brother's dick
over a meter long,
and both of them
completely nekkid forever!
Oh no!
Talk about a terrifying curse.
That definitely qualifies Kaniko
for the position of evil witch.
And I've got just the card.
You misunderstand, this is
but a tragedy born of love.
Making this guy's dick a meter
long is not an act of love!
Now then.
The witch hid herself,
and to find her,
the siblings searched the land,
or in other words,
went on a journey.
So they're on a journey naked.
I guess so.
Then it happened.
Out of nowhere,
one of the witch's creatures
appeared before them
to block their path!
The two ran with
all their might.
While naked.
[HARUTO]
As they both retreated,
they hastily stumbled
upon a cave.
While naked.
The two headed in,
safely out of reach
of the giant creature.
With nowhere to go,
they traveled deeper
into the darkness.
While naked.
Yes, while they were naked!
Where was I?
In the dark depths of the cave,
they found a shining holy sword.
[NAYUTA]
My turn!
The big brother thought
he might be able
to fight off the creature
with this golden sword.
However, he couldn't
swing it properly
due to his new, gargantuan
giggle stick getting in the way.
It was at that moment that the
creature found them in the cave
and reached in,
hoping to catch them
before they were too deep.
This was now
a life-or-death situation.
But the big brother
didn't give up.
"Of course!" he spouted,
"Even if I can't use
this holy sabre,
I can still fight with
this mighty sword of my own!"
[clang]
Dude.
You're kidding, right?
[NAYUTA]
Schwing!
The big brother took hold
of his erect pocket rocket
and wielded it like a sword!
What the hell?
[NAYUTA] Bestowed
with the power of magic,
the big brother's dick
could act as a sword,
grow over three meters long,
and could even function
like a whip
if the situation called for it.
"Thank you, Witch Kaniko!"
he shouted
as he flew past
the big-ass trees.
He aimed his mighty weapon
for the creature's weak point!
Isn't it the witch's fault
they're being attacked
in the first place?
I think...
I can interrupt
with this card now, right?
[NAYUTA]
Oh, it's finally Myaa's turn
to be the storyteller.
This is a really embarrassing
place to pick up.
Maybe I should have waited.
[NAYUTA]
Don't be shy,
just tell us what happens
in the battle
between the big brother
and the giant!
Okay, well...
the big brother, he, uh,
wielded his mighty...
you know, and...
He what?
I couldn't really hear.
Well, I said
he wielded his mighty...
sword dick.
That's it, say it again
but louder this time!
Big brother wielded
his mighty...
He wielded his mighty sword dick
and he used it
to attack the creature!
Are you happy now?
Very much so, thank you, Myaa.
Okay.
The creature was defeated
by the attack
and fell to the ground.
The two siblings then continued
their journey to find the witch,
unimpeded.
While naked!
[CHIHIRO]
And so the journey
of the naked siblings continued.
The big brother fought against
many of the witch's minions,
as well as bandits
and adventurers.
Along the way,
he gained notoriety
as a, um, dick swordsman.
He defeated ruthless titans
and evil dragons,
and even won a duel
against the ultimate
dick swordsman, Musashi.
He wielded two dick swords,
so beating him was a big deal.
The king of the kingdom handed
over his throne to the brother,
and the siblings lived
happily together.
The witch that had cursed them
finally admitted defeat
and apologized for her actions.
The big brother
forgave the witch,
and the two,
plus the younger sister,
formed the first polyamorous
ruling family.
The three lived happily,
and nakedly,
for the rest of their days
in the kingdom that would come
to be known as Nudist Land.
And that's the story of how
this once-normal kingdom
came to have such a strange,
peculiar name.
[ALL sigh]
It's finally over.
Yeah.
Somewhere along the way,
I stopped caring
whether I was gonna win.
We made a pretty awful story.
Yeah, but all the foreshadowing
worked out
and it did get kind of
exciting here and there.
Especially the part with his
Omni-Erectional Movement Gear.
I guess I do feel a little
accomplished for making a story.
And can you imagine turning this
into an anime?
Dude, they'd never
be able to air that.
Oh yeah, obviously.
And we all know who to thank
for creating dick sword.
Oh.
[laughs]
Oh. Is it that late already?
Sorry, everyone,
I gotta go home.
[MIYAKO]
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to miss the last train
if I don't go, too.
I'm gonna hang
and drink some more.
You be safe. 'Kay?
I don't have the energy
to go back to my hotel.
So I'm gonna sleep right here.
[crashes]
She's wiped from
playing around so much.
That kid.
[HARUTO]
Hey, Itsuki?
[ITSUKI]
Yeah?
Why don't you just go out
with Nayu already?
Where did that come from?
She's quite the catch,
that girl.
She's cute, funny,
got a good figure,
and on top of that,
she's a perv.
You know I already
turned her down,
like forever ago, right?
Yeah, yeah, I remember.
You could say I have my reasons.
Such as?
Nothing I feel comfortable
telling you.
Then why even bring it up?
And why do I have to go out
with Kanikou for your reasons?
That's a really weird thing
to say.
What do you mean?
You like Nayu, right?
No, not really.
Where the hell'd
you get that idea?
Hmm.
Stop being so stubborn.
You like her, right?
Then go out.
What the hell's up
with you, man?
You're being pushy.
Guess I am.
[whimpers softly]
All right, fine, I admit it.
I like Kanikou,
just like you said.
Okay, then.
I'm crazy about the girl.
I'd even marry her.
But not yet.
I just can't.
What do you mean by that?
Hypothetically,
and this is
strictly hypothetical.
Let's say Kanikou
and I got married.
What happens then?
Your honeymoon.
Shut up, man.
If Kanikou got married,
the publishers would
lose their minds.
No question.
It might even end up
in the paper or on the news.
[HARUTO]
Well, she is a popular
18-year-old author.
[ITSUKI]
And you can bet the headlines
would be terrible.
"Super Popular Female Novelist
Nayuta Kani Gets Married!"
"She married a man
two years older than her
in the same profession."
Yeah, you're right,
I hadn't thought about that.
Which means...
no one would think of me
as Itsuki Hashima.
I'd end up a supporting
character in her life.
I would just be some writer
who was married to Nayuta Kani.
I don't think
I could handle that.
I want to be the protagonist.
That's why.
Right now, I'm quite
literally a nobody.
But if I can become a writer
who's equal to Kanikou,
then you can bet your ass
I'd tell her I like her myself.
I kinda feel bad.
But I need her to wait
until then.
That makes sense.
Well, what can you do?
[chuckles]
I'm sure it's nice
but there are more
important things
than messing around
with a cute girl.
Aren't there?
But I'm curious.
What exactly do you mean
by being equal to her?
You wanna beat her in sales?
or get some literary award
that she doesn't have yet?
I dunno.
But for now,
I'm gonna at least
try to become
someone more significant
if we ever decide
to get married.
Getting an anime would be a good
first step towards that,
you know?
An anime's just the first step?
Yeah, maybe to you.
You aim high, man.
But still.
You're right.
Considering your
eventual goal here,
an anime's just a checkpoint.
[ITSUKI sighs]
Exactly.
[HARUTO]
Man, this is good.
[ITSUKI]
Yeah, dude,
good call on
the beer and sausages.
[HARUTO]
Speaking of which,
I want to go to Germany,
or Belgium someday.
This girl is
insanely talented.
[phone buzzes]
Yeah?
[TOKI]
Itsuki.
I have something
I have to tell you.
What?
Was there an emergency reprint
or something?
[TOKI]
Oh, you knew about that?
Wait.
Really?
[TOKI]
Yeah, for Kani's new volume,
not "Mahou Academy."
Oh.
The amount of copies you guys
printed for her new book
is already higher
than all of
"Mahou Academy"'s combined.
[TOKI] And she's so popular,
even that wasn't enough.
Did you just call me so you
could brag about her sales?
[TOKI]
No, sorry.
I should probably
congratulate you.
"Mahou Academy" has been
greenlit for an anime.
[ITSUKI shudders]