Across from you,
we have Kaiko Mikuniyama,
a manga artist.
And to her left, Tokuyama,
an editor at Comic Gifted.
Hello. It's a pleasure
to meet you.
[ITSUKI]
Uh, likewise.
So, we brought the two
of you here today
so that you can meet
before the project begins.
If you have any questions
or concerns for each other,
now's the time to voice them.
Don't be shy.
Hey,
this girl looks like she lives
in her own private wing
of a mansion.
Are you sure
she's a good fit for this?
I write some pretty
risque scenes, you know.
Don't worry.
Here are the character designs
and sample pages
we had her draw.
Feel free to take
a look at them.
[ITSUKI]
Whoa. Whoa!
So, what do you think of them?
[ITSUKI]
They're spectacular!
Wow, do you really mean that?
[ITSUKI]
Absolutely!
Thank you so much!
I've been a die-hard fan
of your novels
ever since they first debuted.
So, I was thrilled when I was
offered this opportunity.
-[ITSUKI] For real?
-Yes!
I'm an only child, so I've never
had a little sister of my own,
but I've always wanted
a younger girl to look up to me.
I'm sure you can understand.
So when I started
reading stories
with characters like that,
I became
a little sister enthusiast
before I knew it.
Yeah, that's exactly
what happened with me!
And what really shines
through in your stories
is your true love
for little sisters.
I admire that passion you have.
The description of Hilde's toes
in the scene
where she's walking up
the stairs barefoot
in volume four was true art.
You did not just bring up
the toe scene!
I'm so glad you appreciate
all the hard work
that went into that.
Well, of course, who wouldn't?
Your books aren't like other
little sister series
on the market.
They're just following trends,
but you care!
[ITSUKI laughing]
I completely agree!
By the way, are there any other
little sister characters
you're into at the moment?
[KAIKO]
Well, this is kind of cliche
but from "Eroma"...
That settles it!
Kaiko Mikuniyama,
I can tell that my work
is in good hands with you.
You have my blessing.
I'm honored, Hashima.
I'll give this manga adaptation
100 percent
so that I won't let you down.
[chuckles]
[HARUTO]
Let's see.
Itsuki and I have new volumes
on the shelves.
"Mahou Academy" is getting
a manga adaptation.
"The Spirit Knight
of the Distant World" anime
is about to air.
Miyako and Chihiro
are about to start
a new school year.
Was there anything else
we're celebrating today?
Yeah, Itsuki and I
are getting married!
Will you stop?
All right, then in honor
of all that good stuff,
drink up!
[ALL]
Cheers!
About time your work
got adapted.
I hope the manga
turns out great, man.
Hey, thanks, dude.
But there's no need to worry.
I'm positive
it'll be a success.
What makes you so confident
about that?
Is the manga artist
they assigned you that talented?
Oh, yeah.
Not only is their art great,
but their love for
little sisters rivals my own.
At this point, I'm convinced
there's no one out there
who understands my work
better than Kaiko does.
I swear, that girl
was made for me!
Hold on. You mean, you've been
going on and on about a girl?
Huh?
I guess?
She's "made for you"?
Hey! Don't get the wrong idea!
What I meant is that
she was made
to adapt my story
into a solid manga!
Oh, okay, good!
Then you must mean
that I'm the one meant
for you after all, right?
[ITSUKI]
How is that related?
[NAYUTA] Well, no one
in the whole world
loves you as much as I do.
That's always related!
Sure, but you can't even
spend a full day
talking about
little sisters with me.
So, suggesting you're
"meant for me" is laughable.
I admit that I can't keep up
with your little sister talk
most of the time.
But I'll make up for it
with an excess of love!
[ITSUKI] Hey!
Get off of me, you idiot!
Mind telling me why you're here?
Itsuki let me know that my sake
had arrived and invited me.
For today, let's forget about
our complicated past
and have some fun.
Can you choose your words
a little more carefully?
You're making it sound
like we have history!
I only asked you to do
my stupid taxes last year.
Whatever helps you sleep
at night.
[HARUTO groans]
Anyway, I must say,
this food is simply divine.
I would love to meet the cook.
Oh, uh...
that's me. I made it.
Huh?
-Uh... [chuckles]
-Very impressive,
considering your age.
Why don't you come work
part-time at my place?
I've been in the market
for a skilled chef.
And you definitely pass
the test.
Well, I, uh...
I'll need to get back
to you on that.
[TOKI gulps]
Aah!
I needed this after
two all-nighters!
Wait. So 48 hours straight?
[laughs]
While I appreciate the concern,
us editors have to do this
all the time.
All the time?
I had no idea you had
such a tough job.
It's certainly no walk
in the park.
I have an irregular
sleep schedule.
My job uses me.
My author won't write
his damn drafts.
And my illustrator drops off
the face of the planet!
[TOKI grunts]
But, you know...
it's definitely a job
that's worth the stress.
I think the satisfaction I get
when a new book comes out
is equal to that
of the author's.
-I gotta say somethin' to you!
-[ITSUKI] Huh?
You do good work
when you really try,
so cut the crap
and try from the outset!
[ITSUKI]
Wha...
Shut up. You don't know me!
Maybe I can't do my best
unless I'm feeling the pressure!
[TOKI] Guess I'll have
to fill up your schedule so much
that you'll always feel
the pressure!
[ITSUKI]
You can't be serious,
you sex worker-obsessed freak!
[TOKI]
What the hell does that mean?
I'm not obsessed
with sex workers!
I just respect the fact
that they're trying
-to make an honest living!
-[chuckles]
[doorbell rings]
Hmm.
Guess nobody's home, huh?
Well, that's all right.
[birds cawing]
Shut up, man.
[chuckles softly]
I'm gonna go pick up some water
and energy drinks
from my brother's place.
[NAYUTA] It's getting dark,
so be careful
of perverts out there.
Uhh, I'll be fine!
I'm a guy.
They wouldn't want me.
[SETSUNA sighs]
I wonder if there's
any cool scenery around here
that I can study.
[SETSUNA]
How cute.
Whoa! Look at that ass go!
That's the kind of backside
you only see once in a lifetime!
If I can study those cheeks,
I'm sure I can pull myself out
of this bad butt-drawing funk!
This is my chance!
-H-Hey, wait a sec!
-Uh...
You mean me?
[SETSUNA]
Yeah, yeah, you!
Can I help you?
Will you do me a favor
and show me your ass?
-Wha...
-Ass! Like your butt?
I want you to show it to me.
Come on, I need this!
[CHIHIRO] Uh, what are you
talking about?
I'll never ask
for anything again!
What? You can't be serious!
I don't even know you!
But I am serious!
I've never been more
in my entire life!
Well, I seriously say no!
Hold on, please!
I'll do anything!
Get away from me, you pervert!
Huh?
Booty!
Uhh!
[SETSUNA] I can't have
these clothes in the way!
Just one more layer!
[CHIHIRO]
That's enough!
But the butt!
[SETSUNA groans]
Serves you right, pervert.
[SETSUNA groaning]
[snoring]
[MIYAKO giggling]
Today was a lot of fun.
Hopefully, we'll be able
to enjoy the cherry blossoms
together next year, too.
That sounds like something
a character in a book says
before they end up dead.
You never know how
an author's life will go,
-so let's not joke.
-[chuckles]
That doesn't bother me,
'cause I'll be just fine.
"Mahou Academy's" newest volume
is the best yet.
And now I'm getting a manga!
Everything's coming up roses!
[chuckles]
That's the spirit.
Do your best.
Big brother.
Whoo! Uh-huh!
Don't worry, big brother's
gonna do his very best!
[ITSUKI laughing]
It's about that time,
so I'm gonna head out now.
[ITSUKI]
Thanks for cooking today.
[MIYAKO]
It's late, so be on the lookout
for any weirdos
on the street.
[CHIHIRO chuckles]
Right.
Oh, there's some roast beef
and other stuff in the fridge,
so if you get hungry,
please help yourself.
Awesome.
Thanks, Chihiro.
It's no problem.
And Congrats.
I'll be watching
your anime from home!
[door closes]
Man, you've got
such a nice little brother.
I wish I had him
instead of my sister.
We've been over this.
I could never trade Chihiro
for that animal you call
a little sister.
Hey, "animal"?
I'll have you know that other
than her personality,
she's basically perfect!
Wha...
What do you mean
you're all watching
the premiere
at your friend's house?
-I wanted to watch it with you.
-Huh?
Forget it! Ugh!
You stupid, dumb,
idiotic, bad brother!
Get hit by a truck
for all I care!
And don't bother
ever coming home again!
[groans]
You know what?
Personality is everything.
-Never mind.
-Hmm?
Anyway, we still have
some time before the show.
Why don't we play a game?
Good idea.
[MIYAKO]
What do you want to play?
[HARUTO]
Let's see.
I'm thinking something easy
we can all do while drinking.
What about "Cat &amp; Chocolate:
Blooming Days"?
What kind of game is that?
It's a card-based party game.
The player uses the items
in their hands
to try and solve
the problem drawn.
The next card
in the deck determines
how many must be used.
No exceptions.
The other players then judge
by majority vote
whether the problem
was solved or not.
[MIYAKO] That actually
sounds pretty hard.
[HARUTO laughing]
You'll get the hang of it
once we play.
Let's get creative
with who goes first.
How about the person who enjoyed
their school life the most?
-Sound good?
-I'm not proud of it.
But I had virtually
no friends in school.
I became a shut-in
because I was bullied.
The club I joined fell apart
because of relationship drama
between the members.
Damn writers.
[sighs]
Unlike you all,
I'm actually enjoying
my university life somewhat.
The floor is yours.
We'll continue clockwise
from there on.
Sure, sounds good.
So, I just have to solve
whatever problem
I draw with these items.
Okay.
"I forgot my bathing suit."
Then I'm out of luck.
I guess I'm not
swimming that day.
That's not an option.
You have to use
the items in your hand
to solve the problem.
Oh, right.
I have to use two of them?
Hmm.
[clicks tongue]
Then, first, I'd change
into my gym clothes.
Then...
I'm sorry.
I forgot my bathing suit
at home.
So could I just practice
soccer instead?
I won't fall
for those puppy eyes.
[whistle blows]
Yeah. That probably
would happen.
Hey, it could go differently.
Fine.
Then the entire class
will just have
to play soccer
in the pool today.
And you are to participate
-without clothes on.
-[gasps]
[MIYAKO]
You got it, Teach!
What the hell was that?
[laughing]
I think that's a bit
of a stretch.
But why don't we move on
to the judging?
Survey says...
-[buzzer sounds]
-[MIYAKO whines]
What was I supposed to do
with these cards?
I'm up.
Watch and learn, kids.
"I accidentally called
my teacher 'Mom,'
and it's awkward."
[laughs]
That's pretty embarrassing.
Especially as
a high school student,
that'd be practically fatal.
Back in middle school,
my mom passed away,
so if we're talking
about a female teacher here,
she may have just
reminded me of her.
So that'd make sense.
-[MIYAKO] Uhh...
-Uh-- I--
Oh, man. Sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Uh! Don't worry about it!
I, uh, just have
to use one item.
How about this?
I'd just play it off like,
"I didn't mean you,
I thought I saw my mom
out of the corner of my eye,
but it was just
this anatomical model!"
-How's that?
-Uhh, yeah!
-A plus bro!
-Wow, so creative!
You're amazing, Itsuki!
-Just amazing.
-Yeah.
That works fine.
[HARUTO]
What do we think?
-[bell rings]
-[ALL chuckle nervously]
Okay.
Then it's my turn now.
[HARUTO]
"I can't fix my bedhead,"
and I have to use three items.
[MIYAKO] I have a "hair
products" card in my hand.
It'd be an easy fix
if you had that.
You can't always have the cards
you need when you need 'em.
That's just part of the game.
Okay. Here's item number one.
First, I'll put on a headband.
[MIYAKO]
Oh, that works!
That way you can pull
your messy hair back!
And number two.
-Killifish!
-[MIYAKO] Hmm?
Killifish?
[HARUTO] I'll put the fish
into a fish bowl,
put the bowl on my head,
and skillfully balance it
so it doesn't fall off.
And last but not least.
A guitar!
[MIYAKO]
What, a guitar?
If I go to school
with a bowl of killifish
on my head
while playing the guitar,
everyone will be too distracted
to notice my bedhead!
[MIYAKO] You're right.
They'll just think
you've gone clinically insane!
Still solved the problem!
Let me have this!
Now, what's the verdict?
[buzzer sounds]
Uh! How is that worthy
of a passing mark?
I don't know. It was
pretty funny to imagine.
-Sure was.
-I don't understand you guys.
That makes it my turn.
Let's do it.
Okay. "I broke the window,"
and I have to solve this
with three item cards.
That's my whole hand.
Hmm?
Fine. Here we go!
-Uh?
-Huh?
[MIYAKO] A fire extinguisher,
dumbbells, and a moped?
What are you gonna do
with these?
First off,
I'm gonna grab the dumbbells,
one in each hand,
and swing 'em around
to break
all of the windows
-that aren't broken yet!
-Huh?
What a great sound.
The windows break into hundreds
of glass pieces,
one after another.
Of course, a teacher
tries to stop me,
but as they tiptoe
around the glass,
I spray them in the face
with the fire extinguisher.
Then while they're down,
I smack them
with a dumbbell
to shut them up.
Uhh, N-Nayu?
I'll demolish
the remaining windows and walls
with the empty
fire extinguisher
and blood-covered dumbbells
until I'm fully satisfied.
Then, I'll ride the moped
through the halls,
bringing further destruction
and chaos to the school.
Break, break, break!
[laughs]
Every inch of this damn school
needs to be destroyed!
All of those bastards
who refused to offer me
a shred of help
deserve to die!
Get it together, Kanikou!
Uhh! Whoops.
Sorry, I think the wrong switch
got flipped there, guys.
-Yeah.
-You think?
[HARUTO]
So what's the verdict?
[buzzer sounds]
Huh? No way!
You're the only person
who understands me, Itsuki!
Hey, we all have times
when we just need to let loose.
-I totally get that. Uhh!
-[thuds]
I love you so much, Itsuki!
You're the only person who
was able to help me back then!
I'd let you do anything
you want to me!
Anything! Even your most
deranged fetishes!
[ITSUKI]
No, thank you!
[MIYAKO sighs]
It really makes you think
outside of the box,
but it's a fun game.
Yeah, you gotta get
pretty creative,
so it's great for us writers.
We done? Or you wanna play
another round?
Let's stop, the anime's
about to start.
-[refrigerator door closes]
-Oh.
I guess it's time
for the main event.
Huh?
-You okay?
-[gasps]
Yeah, I was just thinking
about the anime!
[chuckles]
Man, my nerves are acting up.
I wonder how this'll go.
Oh! Don't say that.
You'll make the rest
of us nervous, too.
You're the original creator.
Can't you see
the episode beforehand?
I got what they call
a "white box" copy yesterday.
But I wanted to watch it
for the first time live
as it broadcasts, you know.
Well, let's turn this sucker on
and wait for the show to begin.
[ITSUKI]
Oh. Here we go.
Uh...
[WOMAN on TV]
Next time on "The Spirit Knight
of the Distant World:"
Another Disaster?
What Do You Mean
I'm the Savior?"
See you again next week!
Excalibur!
-[beep]
-[TV switches off]
[laughs]
Uh. Haruto.
[HARUTO] To be honest,
when I got my preview copy
just a day before it aired,
I thought
something like this
might happen.
We didn't have full animation
during recording
for episode one,
and we were still having
script meetings
up until last month.
I wanted to watch it
for the first time live,
but I was also too scared
to watch it any sooner.
[sighs]
And I worked so hard.
Well! That's over!
What do you say
we get back to drinking?
(liquid pouring)
This is the best beer
I've had in my entire life!
It's so good.
Uhh. I'll be honest with you,
I don't really know
what I should say.
But, I mean, we're not writing
to make an anime, are we?
We're writing to make
great novels!
So forget it!
Even if it looks kinda bad.
You can just... ignore it?
Guess you're right.
I could just forget
about the anime
and concentrate
on writing a good story.
If I can bring myself
to do that, life will be great.
Oh, Fuwa.
You know,
my novel's just a product,
and I tend to treat it
like one, too.
I wrote it, researching what
things were popular lately
and gained decent
commercial success.
So if some opinionated reader
calls it uninspired
or a troll says it sucks,
it's generic,
or only sells
because of the art.
I don't care.
It doesn't get under my skin.
Who the hell am I kidding?
I just love them.
Adventure stories
with magic and swords.
Everyone fights over
the pretty girl.
People who try their best
are rewarded.
Stories where the nice guy
ends up happy!
That's why I wanted
to write that.
It's not just
some commercial product.
[sobs]
I love it, God damn it.
How else could I have written
thirteen volumes of it!
You bastards!
To the consumers, this might be
another novel out of many.
But to me, it's unique.
It's dear to my heart.
Why can't you people
understand that?
Damn it!
You can go to hell.
Go to hell.
Go to hell!
[MIYAKO crying]
Huh?
No. Miyako,
why are you crying?
Did I scare you?
Yeah, what do you have
to cry about?
You're not even an author.
Is it something else?
[CRYING]
No.
It's not something else.
Maybe I don't know how it feels
to have a story
I wrote become an anime.
But, but...
[continues crying]
But I do know how sad I'd be
if something I tried so hard on
didn't work out!
[continues crying]
Haruto?
[HARUTO]
I'm gonna go.
I don't want you guys
to keep seeing me like this.
Okay.
[BOTH chuckle]
[HARUTO]
Thank you, Miyako.
[MIYAKO]
I wonder if he's doing okay.
[ITSUKI]
Who knows?
We all worry about
this possibility.
Uh-huh.
And unfortunately,
this is common.
It's tricky to jump mediums.
I had no idea.
But I know
how sad I'd be
if something I tried
so hard on didn't work out.