[groans]
All right, why are you groaning?
Are you stuck
on your manuscript again?
What do you mean
am I stuck again?
And what's stressing me out
isn't the actual story
but the summary.
Oh, so then
you've finished writing
volume five
of "Mahou Academy"?
Congrats.
Save your praise.
I'm only halfway through.
What? Only halfway?
Doesn't it go on sale
next month?
Why are you writing the summary
if you haven't finished
the book?
[ITSUKI] They use it
on my publisher's websites
and for bookstore announcements.
[CHIHIRO] But you already know
what's going to happen, right?
It can't be that hard
to write a summary
of those events,
can it?
I've got the overall idea, yeah.
But I can't be
a hundred percent sure
that what I write
will follow that.
Judging from
previous experience, it won't.
How can you write a summary
of a story that's not written?
Now do you see
why I'm groaning?
I have to capture
the reader's attention
by writing something intriguing
while simultaneously not giving
any plot points away
and do it in a very
limited amount of space.
I'm used to free-form writing,
not following all these rules.
Then there's the fact
I don't know
how things will play out.
[CHIHIRO]
You realize that not knowing
what's going to happen
in your own story
is your fault, right?
[groans]
There's no choice!
I'll just have to B-S my way
through it like I always do!
Did you just say "like always"?
I don't understand
the writing business sometimes.
[NARRATOR]
A few days have passed
since our heroes'
most recent shocking event.
Sieg and Hilde
have finally been able
to return to
their peaceful academy life.
But one day,
they receive terrifying news
that may change
their lives forever.
The siblings vow to uncover
the truth behind this news
with the help
of their closest comrades,
Nobushige and Yuuna.
Together, the four set off
with a particular destination
in mind,
only to find that
they may have been dragged
into an unimaginable incident.
There is a distinct possibility
that a secret
at Vlad Magic Academy
may be revealed soon, as well.
And I just can't shake
the feeling
that there might be
a big change
occurring between
our beloved heroic siblings.
The super popular
little sister academy
battle love comedy continues!
You'll never guess what could
happen in volume five.
And you won't have to,
when it soon hits the shelves
of a store near you!
[HARUTO] I brought you
some special chocolate.
Hmm? Give me one reason
why I should accept
special chocolate from you.
Look.
It's beer?
[HARUTO]
Yup, Valentine's Day beer.
Hence, special.
[ITSUKI]
Then there's chocolate in it?
Nah. But they replicate
the smell of chocolate
using roasted malt.
So basically, it's a stout.
The kind of stout they only make
at this time of year.
And it's damn good.
Want some?
I...
Yeah, I guess.
[HARUTO laughs]
Just look at that covetous face.
You're a dirty boy, aren't you?
[ITSUKI] What are you
talkin' about, man?
It sounded okay,
but I don't need it.
There's no reason to hold back.
You yearn for it so badly
you can't contain yourself.
You want this hard black bottle
to pour some thick,
hearty liquid down
your throat, don't you?
Uh... What?
Don't put words in my mouth.
Come on. Beg for it.
You know you want to.
Begging you would be way
too embarrassing.
What the hell is this?
[HARUTO]
I'm practicing being a dom.
I thought my female fans
would like this kind of thing.
Gotta say, watching you tease
Itsuki like that was pretty hot.
I maintain there was
nothing weird going on,
and he was just
offering me a drink.
[MIYAKO]
Wow, it smells really good.
I agree, so can I have some?
You know the rules.
Stick to root beer, kid.
Okay, okay.
[MIYAKO] Wow. So, you actually
have some on you?
Oh, yeah! Ever since
finding it in Okinawa,
I can't get enough
of this stuff!
Boy, it's got
quite the strong smell.
Sure does!
That's the best part!
You guys ready to find out
if this is any good?
[HARUTO]
Oh, no, hold up a sec.
Huh?
Gotta take a couple pics.
[camera shutter clicking]
[ALL laughing]
[ITSUKI] Trying to show off
your gay appeal again?
[HARUTO] Trying?
More like succeeding.
I've been getting
boat loads of new fans,
so I figure I'll stick
with this routine
until the anime's over.
[MIYAKO]
Must be weird working
with a whole new demographic.
Now you've gotta juggle novel
and anime fans.
That reminds me, I heard
you declined all anime,
live-action, and movie offers
so far, Nayu.
Wow, you did?
And that's not a joke.
Miss Nayuta Kani is
the top-selling author
at our publisher.
Yeah?
Why'd you turn them down?
Because if I took one of them,
I'd end up working a ton more.
I barely have enough time
with Itsuki as it is.
I don't want to throw away days
I could see him.
Yeah, doing an anime adaptation,
like, triples your workload.
There's a meeting every week,
you gotta write side stories
to bundle with the Blu-rays.
And you have
to supervise it all.
As soon as we're wrapped,
I'm gonna need
some serious
tabletop RPG time.
[sighs]
Just like back
when I was in school.
Well, do your best, bud.
Don't drop dead from overwork.
This taste's more like coffee
than chocolate.
Better get something sweet
to pair it with.
-[NAYUTA giggles]
-Hmm?
If that's not a sign
telling me to whip out
my Valentine's Day chocolate,
I don't know what is.
There had better not be
anything weird in them.
I bought them from a store
so don't worry.
Though I did originally plan
to make some of my own
and put a few
secret ingredients in them,
but Myaa vetoed that idea.
Is anyone here surprised?
Not at all.
Thank you for your service.
Hey. Would it kill you
to treat them like a gift
and not like a snack?
Here. Your obligatory
chocolate, Itsuki.
And some for you too, Fuwa.
Oh. That's very nice
of you. Thanks!
[MIYAKO]
This beef stew is delicious!
How is the meat so tender?
[ITSUKI]
It's just leftovers from what
Chihiro made last night.
And it tastes
even better with age.
[HARUTO] Every time
I have Chihiro's cooking,
it blows me away.
I wish I could trade
my little sister in for him.
Oh. So good!
I'm lucky to have such a
talented future brother-in-law.
I swear, he could serve this in
a fancy restaurant if he wanted.
If I'm not mistaken, he added
chocolate to the recipe somehow.
I think he said the polyphenols
would do something to the meat?
[doorbell rings]
Huh?
[ITSUKI whimpering]
It's my editor! Run!
Oh, how nice.
Glad you're having a good time.
Uh...
-And you seem a little worn out.
-[door closes]
That's because I had to go
to Hokkaido to find Puriketsu.
I locked him in a hotel there
for a week
so he would finish
his illustrations.
That doesn't sound
especially legal.
Now I'm back for you!
I'm sure you're aware that we're
well past your deadline, yes?
And I'm sure you're aware
what will happen
if you cause
any more delays, yes?
Uh, yes.
Hey, Kani, Fuwa, sorry about
the unwelcome intrusion.
And I don't believe we've met.
What's your name?
Oh. I'm Shirakawa.
I went to college with Itsuki.
That so?
Then I'm your old classmate's
editor, Toki.
It's a pleasure.
So, what do you want
from me?
I'm not done
with the manuscript.
Don't take that tone with me.
Uh, whatever.
Your readers sent over
some chocolate.
-Sweet.
-Guess I was right
to bring Fuwa's along, too.
Oh!
[laughing]
How does it feel to be
so severely beaten, Haruto?
It feels fine?
Hasn't Fuwa's series sold
more copies
than yours though?
Yeah, but Itsuki's got
a lot of female fans
to get chocolate from.
[laughs]
That's it, give me your energy,
my fans!
I'm so popular right now,
I feel like
I could save the world!
If we're being honest,
they actually like the persona
you've built yourself,
not the real you.
Yeah, you better believe it!
After all, I'm the only one
in the whole world
who loves Itsuki
for his true, perverted self.
[clears throat]
Say what you will, losers.
It doesn't bother me.
Now then, I shall feast upon
the offerings awarded to me
by my leagues
of devout followers!
See, that's how I was hoping
you'd treat my chocolate.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
Let this be a reminder
of how many people
are looking forward
to the rest of your story.
Don't you dare let
them down, okay?
Yeah, I know.
Oh, it's you, Miyako.
Sorry, but I'm expecting
a guest today,
so I can't hang out.
Your editor I met the other day?
No, a tax accountant.
Accountant?
As an author,
I'm essentially self-employed.
So around this time of year,
I do my final return
so I can get
some of my taxes back.
Get some of it back?
What does that mean?
[ITSUKI] So I get paid royalties
from my publisher, right?
Well, before that happens,
a percentage
of what I would be paid
is withheld for taxes.
But in most cases,
you withhold too much.
So when you declare
your actual earnings
in your final return,
the amount you overpaid
in taxes
come back to you.
Oh, wow.
I guess you really are
a functioning adult.
I take offense to your surprise.
So what's this accountant like?
I haven't met them yet.
Though Haruto says
they're really reliable
and experienced with clients
in the publishing business.
[MIYAKO]
Interesting.
Well, good luck dealing
with all your taxes then!
-Oh, and your manuscript.
-Uhh!
[doorbell rings]
Just a second.
You're Itsuki Hashima,
I presume?
Uh, yeah, that's me.
And, uh...
I'm guessing that makes you
my accountant?
Yes, I'm Ashley Ono.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah. It's nice
to meet you too.
Hmm.
Uhh.
You keep this place
pretty clean,
considering you're young
and single.
Well, that's enough chit-chat.
To begin, I'm going to need
to see your payment records
from your publisher.
Yeah. Sure.
Uh...
Huh?
You might want to sit down.
This could take a while.
Okay.
Huh.
You've already taken
the time to sort
all of your receipts by month.
You're more organized
than I expected.
Uh, thanks, I guess.
Now let's see.
Are you registered
at this address?
[ITSUKI]
No, still at my parents'.
Good, that'll work
to our advantage.
Let's treat this as your office
and count the rent
as an expense.
Have a car?
I don't. Not yet.
You should buy
some expensive import one.
That doesn't seem necessary.
Well, I was kidding.
But I do think
you should spend
a little bit more money.
Unlike other freelance jobs,
authors don't have
as many necessary expenses
to write off
[ITSUKI]
For most self-employed jobs,
you have to pay
for tools and materials
to get your work done.
But authors don't have most
of those expenses.
In fact, there aren't
many other jobs
that cost as little
as being an author does.
There's very little
upfront investment.
The more things you buy,
the more things
I can potentially turn
into a tax write-off.
And that's basically how we
accountants prove our worth.
I trust you've written off
those books?
[ITSUKI]
Yeah.
What about
the other paraphernalia
in this room?
Not really, just the stuff
I bought specifically
for research.
Oh my.
So you're a good boy then.
There's nothing I love more
than leading good little boys
like you down
the path of evil.
Wha...
Oh, nothing.
I took the liberty
of doing some research
on your various works.
It seems you're fond
of little sisters.
No, I love them!
Huh.
Well, I believe I've seen
this one somewhere before.
She's the main heroine
of "Oreimo"
and the protagonist's
little sister, Kirino Kousaka.
I'm impressed her influence
has spread far enough
that an accountant
would know her.
And who are these two
scantily-clad young ladies?
The main heroines of "Haganai:
I Don't Have Many Friends,"
Kobato Hasegawa
and Maria Takayama,
both amazing little sisters.
[ASHLEY]
They're the leads?
You'd think the author
is infatuated with young girls.
Yeah, he totally is.
What about the girl
on the left?
The main heroine and resident
little sister
of "Oregairu,"
Komachi Hikigaya!
[ASHLEY]
I'm sensing a pattern here.
I take it all of the figures
you have displayed here
are little sisters?
-Yes.
-That's good.
Then we have plenty of reason
to count them
as research materials.
What? No!
I bought those solely
so I could admire their beauty
from the comfort
of my own home!
I refuse to categorize them
in such a disrespectful way!
Research materials it is.
No! I just can't!
Sweetie, do you want me
to maximize
your tax return or not?
Yes, I do. But...
I cannot sully the beauty
of the little sisters!
If you let me count them
as expenses,
you'll be able to buy
new little sister figures
with the money you get back.
These figures have and always
will be research materials.
Thank you for showing me
the light.
[giggles]
You mean showing you
the darkness.
Oh, I see you have
a lot of games, as well.
I'm not sure I understand
the title of this one.
So... what kind of game
is "Little Sister in Love
with Big Brother
and Masturbates daily
Wearing his Undies"?
That right there is a game
where the little sister
is in love
with her big brother
and masturbates every day
wearing her
big brother's undies.
And this one?
"We're Related,
"We Can't Do Such Things!
"The Beautiful Sister Wife
Getting Absorbed
in a Forbidden Relationship."
What's it about?
To put it simply,
it's about a sister wife
who gets absorbed
in a forbidden relationship.
And just what is
a sister wife?
Someone's little sister who is
also their wife obviously!
Well, that seems
rather complicated.
Let's see.
"Big Brother's
Counter Attack.
"One Year since
Little Sister Was Killed
by a Giant Ant Eater."
That game was a waste of money.
The sister wasn't even in it.
Of course she wasn't.
The title says
she's already dead.
So what's "Fuck-a-Sis?"
It's a game where you fuck
your little sister.
The ending moved me to tears.
[ASHLEY] And "It's Not Strange
for a Little Sister
to Eat Big Bro's Poop, Right?"?
Well, was it strange?
Yes, that's why I liked it.
Looks like you spend the
majority of your money online.
I assume these four-hundred
to six-hundred yen purchases
are digital books?
Yeah, most things
in that price range are.
And here we have
subscription fees
for some streaming sites.
Is that music?
Yeah. Something like that.
What about these
ten-thousand yen charges?
What are they?
Well, other than music,
I might have bought some
magic gems here and there.
And what are those?
It's a currency
to buy loot boxes
on a social network game.
Oh.
All right, and what kind of game
are you using those on?
"Legion of Little Sisters."
If that title
is anything to go by,
I know just what kind
of game it is.
It's pretty much exactly
what you think.
Wait, so can we write off
the gems, too?
Well, that's the plan,
but we can only do so
if you're using it
for your work.
What if it's not for work?
Then you're going
to make it for work.
What? How?
Just have the protagonist
say this in your new volume.
[ASHLEY/SIEG] The odds of me
getting out of this alive
are slim to none.
[SIEG] The chances
are comparable to pulling
an ultra-rare item
from a loot box!
[ASHLEY] You change
the character so he's hooked
on social network games.
[ITSUKI]
I can't do that!
Then it doesn't have to be
the main character.
I believe in my research
I found that there is
a reoccurring villain
who's out to get him?
[CHROM]
Little sisters are nothing more
than a means to an end.
The only things I take seriously
are fighting you
and buying loot boxes
in social network games.
We're ruining established
characterization either way
and making him a joke
of a villain in the process!
Even the hero looks stupid
taking a guy like that
so seriously!
Ruining characterization
a little bit won't hurt.
[ITSUKI]
Yes, it will!
Which is more important,
your tax return
or how perfect your work is?
Obviously how perfect
my work is!
Oh, give me a break.
You authors are all the same.
[ITSUKI grunts]
We're both just looking out
for our livelihoods here.
You leave me with no choice.
I'll have to work my magic
and figure out another reason
to write this game of yours off.
Why were we even arguing
if you could always do that?
I'm so exhausted.
I still don't understand
why she made me give
detailed explanations
of adult games and videos.
Wait a minute, did she do that
so she could laugh at me?
-Hey, Haruto?
-Hmm?
What was with that
sadistic accountant?
[laughs]
She gets the job done.
[sighs]
I guess.
I mean, my refund will be
three times more than last year.
[HARUTO]
Exactly.
[doorbell rings]
-Hmm?
-Uh?
There we go.
Someone's here?
You have a meeting or something?
Not quite.
[HARUTO]
Huh?
[gasping]
I was just stopping by
to return Itsuki's receipts
and give him
a copy of his paperwork.
[giggles]
But I wasn't expecting
to see you here, Haruto.
I wasn't expecting
to see you either!
I haven't forgotten
how much fun we had together
doing your taxes last year.
I have to admit,
I had a little fun
on the side
with Itsuki's as well.
But that was nothing
when compared to yours.
What the hell did she do
to you, man?
She made me explain the plots
of adult games and risque manga.
I feel for you, dude.
She did the same thing to me.
[ASHLEY]
Well, Haruto was different.
The collection
he has is remarkable.
He must have had at least
one hundred naughty games
hidden in his room.
From one man to another,
you're gonna chafe yourself.
What? No, I won't!
It's all just for research,
I swear!
[giggles]
Apparently, your buddy
Haruto here loves maids.
Especially the submissive types
that secretly and gently support
their master from afar.
Playing their role,
yet yearning for affection.
Come to think of it,
you do have a lot
of that character archetype
in your stories.
And somehow they always end up
in maid outfits.
Well. It's, like,
every man's dream
to have a gentle girl
devote herself to him.
I'm just giving my readers
what they want.
But what you like
the most is
taking those gentle girls
who devote themselves to you
and thrusting your desires
upon them.
Showering them in your "love,"
if you know what I mean.
[giggles]
That is so not true!
She speaks lies!
What was it, "Top-Heavy Maid,
Bound and Sticky Four"?
Then there's "Master,
Up My Ass Please,
The Innocent Female Slave,
Genuine Love Edition."
Then "I'll Make You Suck It."
And worth noting is that
the limited edition
includes a download patch code
with maid outfit
pose illustrations,
and you bought it.
Like I said, it's all just
for research, I promise you!
[ITSUKI] And what could
an author like you
possibly learn
from illustration gallery D-L-C?
Don't think I've forgotten
a single thing from last time.
The day you spent hours reciting
every filthy detail
of your collection
was one of the best days
of my life.
[HARUTO] I could never go
through that humiliation again.
Would you still say that
if I told you
I'd put a maid outfit on
next time?
Huh!
I'd be sure to answer
your every beck and call, too.
Fuck me up, Master.
Why do I get the feeling
you just imagined me
in some naughty situation?
I-- I did no such thing.
Oh, but I don't mind.
There's no reason to deny it.
Aah!
[ASHLEY] You imagined me
down on the floor
with my outfit
slowly coming undone.
The image of an innocent,
fair maiden
drove you wild with desire.
Isn't that right?
You're an earnest boy,
so of course
you feel some guilt.
But you just can't stop
your novelist imagination
from picturing
every possibility.
And from this moment forward,
every morning when you wake up,
you're going to imagine me
in the same position.
And despite being plagued
by such guilt,
there's nothing
you can do but satisfy
the physical needs
these thoughts evoke in you,
hating yourself all the while.
Every single day.
Without fail.
[HARUTO]
I wouldn't do such a...
Such a wonderful expression,
Haruto.
It thrills me beyond words
when I see that trembling face.
What am I watching here?
Some kind of kinky roleplay?
-Itsuki, my dear.
-Uhh...
You'll use me again next year,
won't you?
Uh, yeah,
that was the plan, at least.
[giggles]
That's a good boy.
As a reward,
how about I call you,
big brother?
-Hmm?
-That get you going?
You serious?
No way.
[ASHLEY]
As much as I'd like to play
with you two
for a little while longer,
sadly, I have
somewhere else to be.
Oh, what a shame.
Thanks for bringing
the paperwork.
Welcome.
Take this info
on hometown taxes.
A few recommended
donation sites are listed
so take a look
if you're interested.
Thanks.
And for the record,
I like to go for the sake.
I do hope you'll call me
back next year.
Big Bro.
[ITSUKI]
Yes, ma'am!
All right!
Big bro's gonna donate
to a local government
that'll give him sake in return
for his adorable little sister!
Whoa, snap out of it, man!
I know she looks young,
but she's actually 32!
You know what that means?
She's an old hag!
You fool!
Age has nothing to do
with being a little sister!
What the hell are you
talking about, man?
Authors are always
such fun to play with.
I hope you'll entertain me
next time, too.
[giggles]