-Mmm.
-[page turns]
It is freezing in here.
What gives?
I know you've got a heater,
crank it up.
[ITSUKI]
Been broken since morning.
[sighs]
Just when I needed it most.
[MIYAKO]
When's it getting fixed?
Three days.
So for now we're getting by
with this kotatsu,
but it's pretty hard
to concentrate on work.
It sucks.
That's perfect!
Huh?
How about something like this?
Hmm?
Uh... How could I forget
about such a classic?
Hey, it happens.
-Uhh...
-[ITSUKI chuckles]
You wanna go to the beach
in winter?
Well, you see how good
this looks?
I bet the author went to a beach
in Okinawa for research.
-Oh.
-[line ringing]
[HARUTO on phone]
What's happenin', Itsuki?
Hey, Haruto.
Not much, not much.
Just thinkin' about taking
a little trip.
-Wanna come?
-[HARUTO] Huh? To where?
Okinawa.
[HARUTO]
What?
Okinawa!
Ahh--
The temperature is
seventeen degrees Celsius.
It's almost like winter
doesn't exist here.
Ah.
I'm beginning to suspect
that you actually wanted
to come here
to avoid three days
in that ice box
of an apartment.
And how did you convince me
to come with you, again?
Spend all your time complaining
and you won't have any fun.
Cheer up!
It would have been a waste
if you didn't come.
The off-season makes it
cheap to book.
Just like how it's a waste
that Haruto didn't skip
his anime script meeting
to come, too.
[HARUTO]
Man, Okinawa.
I'm jealous.
This beer is good on its own,
but pair it with goya champloo
and it's something else
entirely!
Yeah!
I was trying to imagine what
hibiscus beer would taste like,
but I was way off.
Turns out it's sweet,
tart, and delicious!
Hmm. I wanna have a taste, too.
No. The drinking age
is twenty, remember?
A couple more years and you can
retire your juice box, kid.
You know,
I might as well ask.
Is the fact that you see me
as a kid related
to why you don't see me
as a potential lover?
[spurts]
Uhh...
[coughing]
I'm sorry, I can't hear you
very well.
You're gonna have
to speak louder.
Yeah, you're fighting
an uphill battle
if you want to convince me
that you didn't hear that
when you literally did
a spit-take.
It's not my fault
you weren't loud enough.
Is the fact that you see me
as a kid related
to why you don't see me
as a potential lover?
Was that loud enough
or do you need a hearing aid?
I saw your mouth move
but nothing came out.
Maybe the music's too loud.
I'm going deaf over here.
-I love you, Itsuki.
-[MIYAKO giggles]
What a coincidence,
I love to ski too!
You wanna go out
with me sometime?
Go? We just got here!
-We could just bang.
-I don't know,
I've heard that
gangs can be pretty violent.
-You could fuck my face!
-[MIYAKO gasps]
[ITSUKI]
Pluck your bass?
I'm more of a guitar guy.
All right,
that one sucked, come on.
Yeah, well so did that
confession four puns ago.
Hmm. So more romantic then?
You're as beautiful
as the moon!
Yeah, sure.
Hey. You know this.
It's Natsume Soseki's take
on "I love yo--"
Yes, I do.
It's a quote I recognize
and chose to ignore.
Ah, classic Itsuki.
And that's why I love you...
Boo? You're a ghost now,
I get it.
-[NAYUTA] Hmm.
-[groans]
I'm clearly running out
of ideas, can we stop?
Yeah, fine.
But only if you let me have
some of that beer.
[ITSUKI]
We already said no, but here.
-You can eat one of my eggs.
-[chuckles]
[eating noisily]
[MIYAKO]
Uhh...
I said "eat," not "fellate."
You dog. How can you
just shove your huevos
in an innocent girl's face
like that.
We really ought to do something
about these
extreme fetishes of yours.
I can't believe we bring you
out in public.
[keyboard clacking]
[knocking on door]
Hmm?
The convenience stores
in Okinawa are awesome.
You wouldn't believe
how many different varieties
of hard drinks there were.
Want some?
Just us?
Yeah, Nayu passed out
after bathing.
[ITSUKI]
Hmm.
How is it?
Not too bad.
Hey, Itsuki?
Hmm?
Question:
how do you feel about Nayu?
[ITSUKI]
She's a perv.
Well, yes, but that's not
what I meant.
She says she loves you
all the time.
So, like...
do you ever think about
going out with her?
There's not too much
to think about.
Especially when I gave her
a straight answer ages ago.
Turned her down, of course.
[gasps]
You did?
Back when?
To answer your question
from the other day,
sorry, but I can't
go out with you.
[gasps]
[sobbing softly]
The day after I rejected her,
she started paying me
regular visits.
And here we are.
Oh.
What's that look for?
Well...
until hearing
your side of the story,
I just assumed you were
a jerk leading her on.
I'm glad that's not the case.
I can't believe
you thought I'd do that.
So then is it safe to assume
that you don't have
any feelings for Nayu at all?
That's a silly question.
I'll tell you one thing,
it'd be a hell of a lot easier
if I didn't care
for her at all.
Yeah.
So have you ever read any
of Kanikou's books at all?
Not really.
If you don't have any plans
to become a novelist yourself,
you should
give 'em a chance.
Honestly, you're missin' out
on something good
if you don't.
I mean it.
If you can find the time
to read my stuff,
read hers instead.
It's a better use of your time.
[snoring]
You have been busy.
Haven't you?
[MIYAKO] So it sounds like
we're definitely hitting up
Shuri Castle
and Churaumi Aquarium,
but where else
do you two want to go?
-Deserted island.
-Huh?
Well, there's a part in my story
where the characters end up
on a deserted island.
So I'd like to do some research
for that while I'm here.
Hmm?
I don't know about deserted.
How about a remote one?
Uh!
Check please!
[NAYUTA]
The ocean!
[BOTH laughing]
Ooh, the water's so cold.
I don't care if it's cold. We're
here. We gotta go swimming!
[MIYAKO] How do we do that?
We don't even have swimsuits.
[NAYUTA] We don't need
no stupid swimsuits.
No one's here to see anyway.
Whoa, Nayu what are
you doing? Stop it!
Itsuki! Turn around
and don't look back!
[ITSUKI]
Splash!
Girl! Would you put
your clothes back on?
It's freezing.
Duh! We dipped our feet in it!
Actually, I'm starting
to get used to it.
Come on.
You're turn, hop in!
Stop splashing.
You're getting me wet!
Itsuki, get your butt
in the water!
Don't be stupid.
[laughing]
[MIYAKO[ I wonder if my world
will ever be radiant
and carefree like that.
Sorry, did you say
something, Myaa?
Oh, it was nothing.
Itsuki, I've still got
my eye on you.
I'll break your collarbone
if I catch you peeking!
[ITSUKI]
I'm good, thanks!
[shuddering]
It's so cold!
What's up?
[NAYUTA]
Well, I was just thinking.
It's not like it's
the first time I've noticed,
but your body is well-toned.
Did you used to play sports?
[MIYAKO]
I did karate from grade school
until halfway
through middle school.
Then played tennis,
and was on the basketball team
in high school.
Though I didn't really want to.
[GIRL] You'll never get popular
doing karate.
That's not exactly my priority.
And besides, my sensei told me
that I have a lot of potential.
Whoa. Then are you gonna try
for the Olympics or something?
I don't know
about going that far.
[GIRL] Then just join
the tennis club with me!
It'll be fun!
[MIYAKO] I wonder
what would have happened
if I had stuck with karate.
Maybe I would have been able
to make something of myself.
Or maybe
I would have just given up
at some point along the way
and ended up exactly
where I am now.
Hey, that's cold!
Now you've done it!
[BOTH laughing]
[MIYAKO]
Take this!
Oh, man!
This is so crazy?
That's the sound
of my friends having fun
while I sit here
behind a rock.
[evil laughter]
I've captured
your little sister,
and now she's mine!
Oh!
Prepare... for your demise!
Huh?
Aah!
[crunch]
Megalodon!
[MEGALODON]
It's not like I was trying
to save you or anything.
[scoffs]
Stupid!
It's finally over, big bro.
Now we can get married.
You don't care
that I have sharkskin?
That's never been a problem.
Dude, whoa!
Whoa's right!
This is my new work,
inspired by the whale shark
that shook me
to the core in Okinawa.
Titled: "The Whale Shark's
Little Sister!"
Hell yeah!
This is seriously
some quality stuff!
[laughs]
See, you're a man of culture.
Unlike my editor, who skimmed
and rejected it on the spot.
[SETSUNA] Wait, but how do
their pieces fit together
when they're
from two different puzzles?
I saw a show
about salmon spawning,
and they just sprayed
their seed all over the eggs.
Which is not what we do.
Sharks may be fish, but their
eggs are internally fertilized.
So they've got
the right parts.
For real?
So shark dicks are a thing?
Uh-huh. And I've got it
all planned out.
In the final scene,
when the protagonist
and heroine get together,
it's a beautiful moment
that can only be conveyed
through the eyes of a shark.
Yet my editor refuses to push
the envelope a little.
Give me a second, I got to draw.
Wait, right now?
-Hmm.
-[pencil scratching]
What do you think about this?
Uh...
This looks...
I want some salmon roe.
What? Why's that?
We were just talking about
fish eggs and stuff, remember?
The topic must have
made me hungry, that's all.
Okay, then go eat some.
Oh, you can't tell me
you don't wanna come too!
Hmm?
I thought we would just hit up
a conveyer belt
sushi place nearby.
And somehow, we're here.
[SETSUNA]
We wanted salmon roe,
and Hokkaido's got
the best there is!
[ITSUKI] Then explain to me
why we ended up
at a ramen place!
[SETSUNA]
As we were passing by,
I saw the ramen
and it so looked good,
my stomach changed its mind.
[ITSUKI sighs]
Whatever.
[slurping noisily]
[ITSUKI]
Okay, this is pretty good.
[SETSUNA]
Mm-hmm.
[ITSUKI] You know what?
On second thought,
we came all the way out here,
we might as well make
the most of it.
[wind howling]
[SETSUNA humming tune]
I can't feel my face.
Hey, how much farther do we
have to walk to this hotel?
Hmm? I-I think
it's just up ahead.
I'm dreading
even having to ask this
but you do know
where the hotel is, right?
You worry too much!
I'm, like, seventy percent sure
it's in this direction.
Seventy?
We've got maps, you know.
Let me see.
It's in the complete
opposite direction, you dumbass!
[snoring]
[SETSUNA]
Whoa!
Holy crap!
This seafood bowl is the best!
Damn right,
look at all that shrimp!
-Let's chow down!
[eating noisily]
[ITSUKI chuckles]
There's more salmon roe
than there is rice!
This is ridiculous!
Talk about overkill!
I told you Hokkaido's
friggin' awesome!
Oh, no.
I guess eating half
your weight in sea urchin
and salmon roe
makes you sick.
I always heard that they put
shiso leaves
and pieces of ginger
on top of seafood bowls
to help with digestion
and ease your stomach.
But I had no idea of the pain
that protected me from.
I need a whole plant.
[sizzling]
We still have an hour to kill
before our flight boards.
Oh. That reminds me,
I think I've decided
to stay here for another week.
What?
I figured
I should take the time
to check out the Snow Festival,
since I'm already in town.
And you're just
telling me this now?
You're welcome to stay, too.
No, I think I've had
my fill of snowstorms.
See you later.
I'm gonna go cancel my flight
before it's too late.
I'll stop by
your apartment soon, cool?
Cool.
-[cell phone rings]
-Hmm?
-Yo.
-Itsuki?
If this is about
volume five's draft,
I haven't written it yet.
Don't sound so proud
of yourself.
And while that is a problem,
that's not why I'm calling.
-What, then?
-We're trying
to track down Puriketsu,
have you see him?
You're looking for Setsuna?
Yeah, I was just with him.
Why, is something wrong?
He hasn't sent us
his illustration
for this month's print.
At this rate, we're going
to miss the deadline.
For this month?
That's really bad.
Now tell me where he is.
When I find that brat
I'm gonna kill him,
but not before I get him
to finish this illustration.
Is that so?
Too bad he's gone.
You know that guy,
he just wanders off
and does whatever he wants.
[TOKI]
Non-stop service to Haneda?
Oh, no.
Itsuki,
where are you right now?
-Oh, just Hokkaido.
-What?
Ehh!
Sorry, Setsuna.
Try not to let him kill you.
[SETSUNA]
What gives?
Why won't you let me draw
the illustrations
for your new series?
I've done it before!
Because it's not worthy.
Why are you so full of yourself?
All of a sudden, my art
isn't good enough for you?
No, man!
The opposite.
Opposite?
The fact is,
this new series of mine
just isn't worthy
of your work.
Your art quality
vastly outweighs my story.
So until something changes,
I won't be able to partner up
with you again.
If that's the reason,
I don't mind so much.
Man, it's always fun
when this childish side of yours
comes out to play.
[ITSUKI]
I don't know when,
but someday I'll write
a series worthy of your art.
Wait for me until then, buddy.
[GIRL laughing]
[GIRL 1]
Take this!
[GIRL 2]
Oh, now you've done it!
Geez!
[thunder rumbling]
What the--
Whoa, the temperature dropped
so suddenly.
What's going on?
-[wind howling]
-[girls scream]
-Huh!
-Uh.
[BOY 1]
What is that?
Huh!
Hilde!
[BOY 2]
There's no doubt about it.
This was caused
by someone's magic!
[BOY 1]
I'm coming!
[BOY 2] Sieg, wait!
It's too dangerous!
[SIEG]
I'll be fine!
Some magic blizzard.
Could never hope to sever
the intense bond
between siblings!
Yep.
[grunts]
That's a realistic scene,
if I do say so myself.
Looks like my trips
to Okinawa and Hokkaido
were worth it after all!
Hmm?
I still can't believe
you went to Hokkaido
only two days
after you went to Okinawa.
You're so reckless
with your money.
I'm an author. The research
is worth every penny.
Whatever you say.
Looks great!
Take the first bite.
Whoa! I've never tasted
anything like this!
I'm glad
they're to your liking,
'cause I had to get
a little creative.
I used the chiraga
you got from Okinawa
and the crab you got
from Hokkaido.
Well, there you go.
That explains it.
The fat from the pork
and the juices from the crab
play well off each other.
And there's this
harmonious trio of texture.
The crispy wrapping,
the juicy, tender crab,
and the crunchy chiraga.
These ingredients
from north and south Japan
make this such a unique dish.
We've gotta think
of a name for it.
The South.
Down-South. Southern.
Wait, what about the North?
We need both.
The Southern Northern.
SouthNorth.
No, The NorthSouthern. Ehh.
"North and South
Spring Rolls" works.
Well, whatever they're called,
they're unusual.
[door opens]
[CHIHIRO]
I'm going now.
See you later!
[ITSUKI]
Later.
I wish that you'd come home
every once in a while, big bro.
Why would I do that?
[chuckles]
Oh, yeah.
Here, I bought some souvenirs
for the family.
Different chocolates
you can't get here.
[chuckles]
Thanks, this is
really thoughtful!
I'm sure Mom and Dad
will be ecstatic.
Oh, and you can have this too,
if you want.
Wow!
Thanks a bunch!
A whale shark.
Hey, now we have
matching phone straps!
[ITSUKI]
Yeah.
Be careful getting home.
[CHIHIRO]
I will. Goodnight!