[typing]
[sighs]
The reviews and comments
for episode two are horrible.
And I doubt
it's gonna get any better.
I'm completely done for.
Why did I even work
so hard on it?
And you have
to supervise it all.
As soon as we're wrapped,
I'm gonna need
some serious tabletop RPG time.
I got a job for you, Haruto.
[HARUTO]
Huh?
I wanna play a TRPG,
so I need you
to be the gamemaster.
[HARUTO]
That came out of nowhere.
I've been thinking about
trying one for a while now.
And you seem like you have
the time on your hands.
[Haruto] Uh, I still have
quite a bit of work
on my plate, man.
Well, guess what?
I don't care.
[sighs]
All right.
Could be fun.
Not like I have a choice.
Cool.
We need more people,
so I'll text Kanikou,
Chihiro, and Miyako.
Sure.
Sounds good.
Um, so TRPG stands for
Tabletop Role-Playing Game?
I can't say I've ever heard
of that before.
I've heard of the term,
but that's about it.
I've read a retelling
of a campaign before
but never actually
played anything myself.
Well, a TRPG is a game
where you advance
by interacting with characters
within a world
and roll a dice to determine
how your decisions
and actions pan out.
Each player creates
their own character
and participates in the story
presented to them.
Most of the events will be
determined by the GM,
or gamemaster.
But depending on what
the players choose to do,
the story could take a turn
that even the GM didn't expect!
Are we allowed to make
a character
that's completely different
from us in real life?
[HARUTO]
Of course.
Playing as someone different
is one of the biggest appeals
of any RPG,
but there's nothing wrong
with making your character
exactly like yourself.
Exactly like myself?
[HARUTO] The world for this game
is your typical one
of swords and magic.
You're all adventurers
who have just arrived
in a new kingdom.
With that out of the way,
let's create some characters.
I've taken the liberty
to make samples
of partially
predetermined abilities.
To make things easier,
we'll use them as templates.
[CHIHIRO]
Hmm.
[MIYAKO]
Hey, Fuwa?
I'm having trouble
understanding my sheet.
What does the "2D" and "3D"
next to our stats mean?
The "D" is for "dice."
You'll make various decisions
throughout the game
by rolling your dice.
The higher
the corresponding stat is,
the more of them
you'll get to use.
[MIYAKO] So then "2D"
means you roll two dice,
and "3D" means you roll three?
[HARUTO]
Exactly.
Silly question.
But can we pick
whatever sex we want?
Sure can.
So does that mean you're gonna
make a female character too?
Wait, you're not going
with a guy either?
Her name is Tsukiko,
and she's a seventeen-year-old
female knight!
Well, if you're doing it,
I might as well do it too.
And while we're at it,
why don't I make my character
your character's little sister?
Her little sister?
So you'd be
my little sister then?
I guess there's no reason
for me to say no.
Good! 'Cause I'm making
my character
your little sister, too!
She'll be the youngest
of the bunch!
And her hobby is doing
naughty things with Tsukiko!
[ITSUKI] That's not a hobby,
that's a problem!
Is that against the rules?
[HARUTO]
Uh, not exactly, but...
Yeah, whatever,
do what you want.
Huh?
If you three are going
to be sisters on an adventure,
then I guess I might
as well be one, too.
I can make my age twenty,
like I am in real life,
and that'll make me
the oldest of the bunch.
I like the idea of you
as an older sis.
[laughs]
Hold on a sec.
I'm your little sister?
[MIYAKO]
You would be, yeah.
I'm the little sister?
You're okay with that, right?
Considering your
freaky obsession?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I love little sisters and all,
but that doesn't mean
I actually want
to be one myself!
That's completely different!
Then do you want me
to make my character younger?
[grunts softly]
I guess this could work.
Well, what do you know?
Five seconds of thought
and you're back on board.
You better take
good care of me, big sis.
You're playing
the part a tad cockier
than necessary.
And let me gear up some music
for the opening.
-[phone beeps]
-There.
-[fanfare playing]
-Gagagia Kingdom:
a small domain that rests
on the edge of the continent.
Within its boundaries lie
many ruins and caves.
Countless adventurers
travel here
seeking treasure and materials
from the native monsters.
And now,
four adventuring sisters
have arrived in the kingdom.
Will fate be kind to them?
There's only one way
to find out.
End scene.
Now, please introduce
the characters
you've created to us all.
Okay, how about I start
since I'm the oldest?
My name is Miyako,
just spelled differently.
And I'm an expert
on attack magic.
I also have this
one particular special attack
where I can shoot coins
at a super high velocity.
I'm Tsukiko, the second sister.
I'm a female knight
with long black hair
who fights with her sword
and shield.
My special ability
is I can reproduce any weapon,
as long as I see it once.
[CHIHIRO]
I'm the third sister, Sen.
I'm a thief class
who uses bows and arrows
as well as knives to fight.
And I have the ability
to open treasure boxes.
I can nullify any magical attack
that touches my right hand.
Everyone is using skills
that I'm pretty sure
I've seen somewhere before,
is that okay?
It's not like our campaign
is gonna be made into a book
or an anime, so it's fine.
Well, in that case.
Last but not least,
I'm the youngest sister,
Death Mask.
When I come in contact
with another's bodily fluids,
I can increase
their abilities tenfold.
[giggles]
Something tells me your skill
is gonna cause the most trouble.
All right,
let's start the story.
You've all arrived
at the castle town
in Gagagia Kingdom.
It's early afternoon,
and the main street
is bustling with people.
Okay, team, what does
everyone want to do?
I say we go to the inn
and relax by exploring
each other's private parts,
eh, Tsukiko?
Ten seconds in?
[HARUTO]
Unfortunately, you've used up
all of your travel money
on your way here.
With what you have now,
you won't be able
to sleep at any inn.
[CHIHIRO]
Makes sense.
That just means
we'll have to find
a way to make money, right?
[MIYAKO] How do we
make money in this world?
[HARUTO]
If you go to the pub,
you can find some job listings.
Or you could go to some ruins
and find treasure.
Or defeat monsters.
Then exchange whatever
they drop for money.
You heard the man.
Let's head for the ruins.
Who knows what
we'll find in there?
Wouldn't working be a safer bet?
You're so busy discussing
what to do next
that you hardly noticed
the four men
that appeared before you.
They seem to be adventurers.
[chuckles]
Sounds like you ladies
are low on funds.
But we'd be happy to treat
all of you to some drinks
and a room, what do you say?
Whoa, what? Seriously?
[THUG cackles]
Of course.
How lucky are we
to run into such generous guys?
We accept your offer!
Hey! Let's think
about this, big bro--
I mean, big sister!
They obviously have
other intentions.
I shouldn't have
to tell you this,
but don't go with them.
Really? Are you sure?
Oh, come on, we just wanna show
you a good time, I promise.
How dare you trick me
with the intention
of doing lewd things to us!
[chuckles] What?
Are you going to try
and fight us, little girl?
[MIYAKO]
We don't have much other choice!
The four of us will have
to stomp you into the ground!
This might actually
be good for us.
If we beat them,
we can steal their money.
Color me surprised
that you're talking
about robbing
these dudes so casually.
Sen is more hardcore
than I expected.
Either way, you girls
have decided
to fight
these shady characters.
I'll make some
battle preparations.
Give me a sec.
This is Tsukiko.
-This is Sen.
-[CHIHIRO] Huh.
[HARUTO]
This is Miyako.
And this is Death Mask.
Why am I the old geezer?
All of their faces
are very stoic.
This is a western TRPG,
so we're gonna have to work
with what we've got.
These four are your enemies.
We'll take turns.
Order is determined by agility,
so highest goes first.
All right.
Let your battle begin!
[grunting]
[THUG laughs]
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to fight back?
I'll rip your clothes to shreds!
Ha-ha. Wide open.
[screams]
I've had just about enough
of you guys!
Ice Needle!
You won't beat us that easily.
Didn't work.
-[THUGS laugh]
-[ITSUKI] Damn, they're strong.
If we don't change things,
we're gonna lose.
Myaa, you know
what we have to do!
Are you ready?
Sorry, what?
I'll use my ability.
We'll power you right on up!
Then, you should be able
to defeat them
with one blast from your magic!
You can't fool me!
I know your ability
requires us
to do pervy fan service.
-No, thanks!
-[NAYUTA] Don't worry.
We just have to share
a little kiss.
[MIYAKO] Really? Well,
I guess that's okay then.
For the team.
-Then here comes the loving!
-[MIYAKO gasps]
[NAYUTA] Slipping past
my big sister's soft lips,
my tongue met hers.
The two twisted together
in a vulgar dance.
And unable
to help herself anymore,
Miyako lets out
an unstifled moan.
-[ITSUKI grunts softly]
-[MIYAKO moans]
I'm sensitive there.
I'd appreciate it
if you didn't fabricate
my character's reaction!
[NAYUTA chuckles]
[NAYUTA] You're so cute,
I could just eat you up.
As I devour Miyako's tongue,
I gently untie
the strings of her robe.
"No, you mustn't."
I ignore my sister's
weak cries of resistance
and proceed to take off
her robe and underwear.
I strip naked myself,
and our bodies press together.
As she quivers,
partially in embarrassment,
but mostly from excitement,
I kiss her deeply.
She writhes in a fit
of her own pleasure.
You can feel it swelling up.
Can't you, big sis?
I aggressively attack
my big sister's
various weak spots.
To which she responds
with a chorus of sweet moans
each and every time.
Uh, what the hell
are we looking at here?
[MIYAKO/NAYUTA moaning]
-[SOLDIER] Hold it right there!
-[ITSUKI] Uh...
[HARUTO] Uh, a number
of soldiers head your way,
sporting armor and spears.
[THUG] Oh, no!
Let's get out of here!
[HARUTO] Fearing the soldiers,
the four opposing adventurers
decide to flee.
[ITSUKI sighs]
Looks like we're saved.
[HARUTO]
In your moment of relief,
the soldiers surround you.
[ITSUKI]
What?
[SOLDIER] You're under arrest
for public indecency!
You've got it wrong!
Me and my big sister here
were just performing
filthy, depraved acts
on each other
in the middle
of a public street!
Yes. Public indecency.
Oh, that's right.
I didn't agree to any of this!
[cell doors slam]
[MIYAKO cries]
I never thought
the day would come
where I'd be arrested
for public indecency
of all things.
What happened?
Where did I go wrong?
Well, we're certainly not
helping the situation by moping.
Let's put our heads together
and come up with a plan.
I've had enough of your plans!
-[WOMAN] Um, pardon me.
-[BOTH] Uh?
[ITSUKI] Huh?
Who the hell are you?
I'm Silvia.
The princess of Gagagia Kingdom.
And I have come here to ask
a favor of you adventurers.
If you will do this for me,
I can promise you
an immediate release in return.
I don't see any other way out
at the moment.
Let's listen to her.
So in summary,
we just have to deliver
a letter to the sage
living in the forest?
We're like a delivery service.
Sounds simple enough to me.
I don't know.
Haruto's novels usually try
to surprise you
by taking mundane events
and turning the tables.
There's probably
something more to this.
Like, the princess is a villain
who's setting us up.
And the sage we're being sent to
is an evil wizard who'll use us
as sacrifices
to revive some nastier deity.
All right, that's enough!
Stop trying to predict
what's gonna happen in my story!
[snarling]
Looks like we've got company!
Are goblins high level enemies
in this world?
Good question.
Perhaps someone could
use their wisdom
to figure that out.
Okay, then I'll do it,
since mine is the highest.
[HARUTO]
Success.
Goblins are one of
the weakest monsters
in the kingdom.
You should have no problem
defeating them.
Also, they're weak against fire.
Everyone ready?
Let's rip 'em a new one!
Yah!
Here comes a fireball!
[GOBLIN groans]
[chuckles]
[HARUTO] Since you
have defeated the goblins,
your journey continues.
Further in the forest,
you spot a beautiful, vast lake.
[NAYUTA]
Now that we've found this lake,
it'd be a waste
if we didn't go for a swim!
[ITSUKI]
Huh?
If we relax here for a bit,
are we gonna get
some health back?
[HARUTO]
Yup.
Then we should definitely
stay for a while.
I hope this isn't a trap
set up for us.
Oh, it'll be fine!
Besides, what could be
so dangerous
about such a pretty lake?
I've seen a lot
of shark thrillers
and monster movies
in my time.
And the first ones
to die are usually
the unsuspecting girls
in bikinis.
[screams]
[CHIHIRO] Yeah, I've noticed
a similar trend
in the campaign retellings
that I've read.
Something bad always
seems to happen
when the girls are showering.
-[roars]
-[screams]
Oh, those ones?
Those games are based
on the Cthulu mythos.
You're in for a lot gore,
horror, and scenes like that
when you step into
that kind of world.
This game is
a peaceful fantasy though,
so nothing that dangerous
will happen.
[ITSUKI]
I don't believe you.
[HARUTO] Then why don't you
use your intuition
and roll the dice?
I think you can sense
if there's any danger or not.
Hmm?
[dice rattle]
[HARUTO]
Yup.
Now that you've had
a look around,
there's nothing to worry about!
[NAYUTA]
That settles that!
It's time to hop in the water!
Everyone ready to strip naked?
Oh, how am I not surprised?
Wait a second,
do I have to strip, too?
There is no need
to be embarrassed, Sen.
We're all family here,
remember?
[CHIHIRO]
I guess you're right.
You better not be thinking
anything weird.
[splashing]
Uhh...
[blows bubbles]
-That's when it happened!
-[gasps]
[roaring]
[screaming]
I told you this was a trap!
[HARUTO]
The creature that arises
from the water is the Roper.
It has a single eye
and multiple tentacles
protruding from
its cylindrical body.
I'm not gonna lose
to some stupid tentacles!
No.
No, don't do that.
Your slimy appendages
don't belong in there.
I don't have any of my knives.
What are we gonna do?
That's why I prefer magic!
Energy bolt!
Not a chance, monster!
I can't beat it alone
if it regenerates!
[chuckles softly]
Then it looks like
it's time for me to use
the ace up my sleeve!
Huh?
Unlimited...
Blade Wo-- just kidding.
I'll use my "Phantom Smith"
to produce a sword!
[grunts]
Thanks a lot, sis.
You saved me!
But why didn't you cut
yourself loose first?
[chuckles softly]
As your older sister,
I prioritize you.
Your safety comes first.
Big sister!
Yeah, uh, hello?
I'm your little sister too,
you know.
Why would I save you
from something you enjoy?
Well, if he won't save you,
then I will, Death Mask!
That's it.
Suddenly I'm in the mood
for some calamari.
[HARUTO]
Turns out you were wrong
about this place being safe.
But the lecherous Roper
has been defeated,
and you can relax
for real this time.
Good job!
You just had to insert
your weird tentacle fetish
somewhere,
didn't you?
[ITSUKI] So I guess
this is where the sage lives?
[NAYUTA] Yeah. It's literally
emitting evil smoke.
[MIYAKO] There are probably
traps everywhere.
But if we want to deliver
the letter,
we're gonna have to go
in at some point.
What's written
in that thing anyway?
Have we tried to read it yet?
No, because Silvia told us
we absolutely
can't look inside--
Just tear it open!
I'm down.
[grunts softly]
Fine.
This is what's written
on the paper.
"I'm delivering four young girls
to you as sacrifices.
Please accept them."
This is exactly
what I said would happen!
Well, then what are we
gonna do?
There's no sense in going in,
knowing we're just
gonna be sacrifices.
I agree with you.
So why don't we just burn
the mansion
to the ground instead?
Uh!
[tape fast forwarding]
[NAYUTA moaning]
-[explosions]
-[WIZARD screams]
[WIZARD]
Curses.
We were so close.
-It looks like I'll have...
-Shut up.
...to deal with you mysel--
[ITSUKI] Princess Silvia!
Give it up!
We've already put
a stop to your plans
to revive the evil deity
so you could take the throne!
It's over!
I thought you were just a bunch
of kids, so I let my guard down.
But I won't make
the same mistake twice!
[roaring]
You can't trick us
with your illusions!
It's a good thing I have more
than just magic at my disposal!
Roper's tentacles!
Huh?
Wait. What the hell
did you do?
[chuckles]
I can reproduce any weapon
I've laid my eyes upon.
And that includes
a monster's tentacles!
How dare you. Unhand me!
Please! I beg you!
Let me go this instant!
Oh, my!
Come on, Myaa,
while she's distracted!
This is our chance
to power you up!
That's not happening.
[HARUTO] And so the four sisters
successfully put
a stop to the conspiracy
that threatened the kingdom.
Our heroes can now get
some well-deserved rest.
This concludes our adventure.
[ALL]
Good work, everyone!
Nayu may have given me
a hard time,
but I'm glad
I tried TRPG.
They're so fun!
[CHIHIRO] Yeah. I'd like
to play one again.
I'm really glad
you had a good time!
It wasn't bad, but I didn't
get to power up
Itsuki's character even once.
I'll have
to try harder next time.
I would prefer it if you didn't.
[chuckles]
All right, well.
I'll start thinking
about our next campaign, then.
Looking forward to it.
And you need to start thinking
about learning
some self-respect.
[NAYUTA]
Oh, come on.
I didn't hear your character
complaining about it,
Miss One-Woman-Army.
-Thanks for this, Itsuki.
-Hmm?
What do you mean?
The game we played today,
it was all to cheer me up,
wasn't it?
Mmm. D-Don't get
the wrong idea, man!
I just had a sudden urge
to try a tabletop RPG!
-Yeah, that figures.
-[scoffs]
You know...
it's a lot of fun
to create something.
And it makes me happy when
people enjoy what I've made.
No matter how much
or how little.
I bet it's the same for them.
My anime team.
Sure, there some
rough times along the way.
And in the end,
it didn't pan out.
But the fact that we all
worked hard on this thing
wasn't a waste.
At least, I think.
So there's no reason
I should stop giving
a hundred percent now, right?
No, man.
Yeah.
-Hey, Itsuki?
-Huh?
Does Miyako have...
a boyfriend
or what?
Huh?