-Oh. Hey, Itsuki!
-[gasps]
Oh, good, it's just you, Miyako.
On your way somewhere?
Karaoke.
-By yourself?
-Yeah.
Well, in that case,
do you mind if I tag along?
[MIYAKO]
So, aren't you gonna sing?
No, I'm way too busy
to be fooling around.
I don't really understand
why we're here then.
Duh. Because it's safe and he'll
find me at my apartment.
-Who will?
-You know, my editor.
I take it your deadline
is fast approaching, then?
Well, one of them is.
In actuality,
there are two deadlines.
Okay, now you've lost me.
[ITSUKI] There's the deadline
where you have some wiggle room
in case some unforeseen
circumstances arise:
The tentative deadline.
But then,
there's the dangerous one
that, if missed, may prevent you
from releasing your book:
The true deadline.
[MIYAKO]
I feel like I know the answer,
but which of those
are you about to miss?
The true deadline.
Itsuki.
-[MIYAKO gasps]
-No way!
How'd you find me?
In preparation for this,
I messed with
your phone's settings
so I'd be able to locate you
any time I need to.
I'm pretty sure
that's illegal!
I'd do anything for the sake
of releasing a book.
Just like a good editor should.
Now get your things.
You're writing at the office
and you're not leaving
until you're done.
Let go of me!
Picking me up like a kid.
I'm a proud man,
and I will not have this!
[TOKI]
Oh, you're so proud
of missing
your deadlines constantly?
Come on, dumbass. Let's go.
[ITSUKI]
Just hear me out, man.
[grunting]
-Sorry for making a scene.
-Ow, ow, ow!
Your name is Shirakawa,
I get that right?
The next time this ass tries
to run away from his work,
do me a favor
and let me know.
[MIYAKO]
Uhh... will do.
I don't get
the writing business.
Like, for real this time.
Now, I'm sure you're wondering
why we called you in today.
Are you familiar with this title
by any chance?
[GIRL]
"Mahou Academy."
Yes. I've heard
of this one before.
[ringing]
[MAN] Hello, this is GF Bunko's
editorial department.
Oh, hello!
It's nice to hear from you.
Yes. Yes,
thank you again for that.
I appreciate it.
[HARUTO]
Well, if there's one thing
people should be looking
forward to the most,
it's the intense battle scenes
that you can only see
in a visual medium
like an anime.
-[ITSUKI] Let me go!
-[TOKI] You know I won't!
-Give it up!
-[laughing]
My, they're a bit noisy
next door, aren't they?
[groaning]
You're not going home
until you finish writing this.
[sighs]
This is pointless. I'll never
be able to finish in time!
I might as well run away.
[elevator bell dings]
[ITSUKI]
Uh...
What are you doing
in that box, dude?
Oh, it's just you, Setsuna.
You running away
from the same guy I am?
Nope. I just had
a regular meeting today
and was about to head home.
Aren't you lucky?
Oh! I just got an idea!
Why don't you and me get outta
here and go booty-watching?
Huh?
[ITSUKI] Well, here I am.
In a mixed-bath hot spring inn.
My editor's gonna kill me
if he finds out.
But he can't. I turned off
the GPS on my phone,
so my virtual shackles
are gone.
Are you ready to rock?
We have a batch
of booty soup waiting!
So we're doing this?
I can't tell if you're joking.
[SETSUNA]
Of course we're doing it!
[sighs]
Why do you want to see these
poor girls' asses so badly?
-Reference and motivation!
-What do you mean?
Well, you know that I'm drawing
a lot of tail in the series
I'm currently
working on, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
But what about it?
As of late, all my buns
have been comin' out the same.
It's like I've hit some sort
of artistic butt rut.
So naturally, I want to stare
at some new asses
for inspiration!
Uh?
[ITSUKI] I guess even he hits
a creative wall sometimes.
[SETSUNA humming]
Why must you betray me
like this?
Huh? What's that?
Nothing.
[SETSUNA]
I never noticed before,
but you've got
a pretty cute butt.
I would hope
you've never noticed!
[chuckles]
Okay, let's get going!
I'm right behind you.
Huh!
Uhhh!
Would you look at that?
We've got some strapping
young men joining us.
[cackles]
You're absolutely right.
Isn't that something?
We rarely get them here.
[cackles]
Hello! You sure picked
the best spot, huh?
Hey! Setsuna!
Where did you two
darling boys come from?
Just Tokyo. And you ladies?
How sweet.
He called us "ladies!"
It's been about three years
since the last time
someone called me a lady!
Sure you don't mean thirty,
octogenarian?
Sorry you came all the way here
only to find us shriveled,
wrinkled old hags around.
You don't have to be sorry.
All girls are beautiful.
No matter the age!
Oh my, you sure know
the quickest way
to an old woman's heart,
don't you?
Oh, he better slow down.
Any more sweet talk and I'm
gonna take him home with me.
-My, my... [laughs]
-Hey. You there!
Why don't you come join
your friend over here?
Nothing to be afraid of dear.
We don't bite.
Hard anyway.
[cackles]
No, I'm fine out here!
Don't mind me!
Don't be shy. Hop in.
[OLD WOMEN laughing]
-We won't hurt you.
-Hold on.
[cackling continues]
Uh, S-Setsuna!
I'll catch you later, man!
I'm going to the men's bath!
[sighs]
I bet going to a hot spring
with Itsuki would be great.
Yeah. Just the two of us
without any clothes on.
[giggles]
[ITSUKI sighs]
That was legitimately
horrifying.
[sighs]
-[rattling]
-Hmm?
You?
Wait, but how?
I turned off my GPS!
I thought you might do that.
So I took the liberty
of putting
a tracking device
on your clothes.
Where'd you even get that?
I told you before...
if it's to get this book out,
I will do...
whatever it takes.
[ITSUKI whimpering]
[screaming]
[grunts]
What gives?
This will be your workplace
for the foreseeable future.
You've gotta be kidding me.
What--
What fresh hell is this?
This is a special room
where we trap--
where we put
authors and artists
so they can concentrate
on their work.
You can't be serious!
I refuse to work
in this dungeon!
Why can't you just put me up
in a hotel room
like you do with Kanikou?
Only authors who have had
their work made into anime
or top the sales charts
are awarded such luxuries.
You've got three days.
That's when we hit
the real final deadline.
-Got it?
-Uhh...
What happens if I don't make it?
I'll kill you.
You'll... You'll what?
[TOKI]
You heard me. See ya.
I'll let you out
once you've finished.
Hold on a minute!
How am I supposed
to go to the bathroom?
[ITSUKI]
Don't tell me.
Feel free to use
that box at your leisure.
Just think of it
as another way
to maximize
your remaining days for work.
Can't have you wasting time
walking down the hall.
This is insane!
Let me out of here!
I mean, please let me out!
I'll be good. I promise!
[sobbing]
Please!
This can't be real.
Did he actually lock me
in this prison cell?
The only choice
I have is to write.
Uh...
[groans]
[cackling]
[evil laughter]
Uh!
What the hell
are these monsters?
[roaring]
[SIEG]
My hands are shaking.
Am I actually experiencing fear?
[roars]
[screaming]
[ITSUKI grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[typing]
[ITSUKI]
I have to hurry up and finish,
or I'm gonna die.
[panting]
[SIEG] I don't want to die.
Hilde. Hilde!
[snickers]
You look pathetic, vermin.
It's Chrom!
I'm not letting you
escape me again.
This is where you die, Sieg!
[roaring]
[shuddering, screaming]
[TOKI] I'm not letting you
escape me again, Itsuki!
[screaming]
Just a dream.
A dream?
I wasted all that time.
-[HARUTO] Hey!
-Huh?
-Itsuki!
-Haruto?
You okay in there?
[ITSUKI]
I'd be lying if I said I was.
You sound so defeated, man.
You know, you might
get away with giving up.
The editors aren't
completely heartless.
If you honestly can't do it,
I'm sure
they'll delay the release.
That reminds me, your new volume
comes out in March too, right?
Yeah. But mine's already
well past the revision stage.
[grunts]
So, what are you gonna do?
Wanna give up?
Not yet. I'll keep
grinding away for a while.
All right. Good luck.
Thanks.
I'm gonna finish this
as fast as possible
so I can escape this hellhole.
[chuckles]
By the way, they don't let you
use cell phones in there, right?
Want me to deliver any messages
to Chihiro or Nayu for you?
[ITSUKI]
Hmm?
Just tell them not to worry.
Roger. Well, you can do it.
Okay. I'm not letting them
get any further ahead of me.
[typing]
[ITSUKI] Somehow, I made it
to the climax in one piece.
But I can't write a scene
that I'm satisfied with.
Damn it!
I'm so close to finishing this!
-[HARUTO] Itsuki.
-Uh?
I didn't think
you'd come back again.
Well, I had
to deliver your gifts.
First, a lunch
that Chihiro made for you.
I made some food.
Can you take it
to my big brother for me?
Sure thing.
I bet it'll lift his spirits.
I hope so.
I know it's not much,
but I want to help
any way that I can.
Though I'm sure my brother
will be fine no matter what.
Chihiro.
[HARUTO]
And second, some more
Valentine's chocolates
from your readers.
-Better late than never.
-[ITSUKI] Ohh!
Thank you so much
for bringing me these.
Also, tell Chihiro
I said thanks.
Will do. Hey,
let's all get together
for drinks at your place soon.
[ITSUKI]
Yeah.
Whoa!
Huh?
Uh!
[MIYAKO] Do your best
on your manuscript.
[NAYUTA] When you get back,
let's go to a hot spring.
From your loving wife.
[chuckles]
Whatever, kid.
[moans]
Oh, man, this is so good!
[eating noisily]
Oh, this chocolate
is delicious too.
All right.
This battle decides my fate!
[CHROM laughing]
It looks like this will be
the end of your story.
Now doesn't it, Sieg?
[SIEG gasping]
Ah!
[panting]
[NOBUSHIGE]
Are you giving up, Sieg?
[YUUNA] If my brother thinks
you're strong, then so do I!
[HILDE]
You can't lose, big brother!
I want you to come back to me!
[SIEG]
Hilde.
[ITSUKI] When this is over,
I want to eat
Chihiro's delicious food again!
[SIEG] When this is over,
I want to eat
Hilde's disgusting food again!
[ITSUKI]
I want to drink and play games
with Haruto and Miyako again!
And go on trips with Setsuna!
[SIEG] I want to spar
with Nobushige and Yuuna again!
[ITSUKI] I want Ashley
to call me "big brother" again!
[SIEG] I want Hilde to call me
"big brother" again!
[ITSUKI]
I want to see Kanikou again!
[SIEG]
I want to see Hilde again!
No matter what, I'm going
to make it back to Hilde.
I refuse to be beaten by you!
[ITSUKI] I'm going home,
getting drunk, and going to bed!
I refuse to be beaten
by this deadline!
That's impossible!
How do you have
the strength to stand?
How can you still
bring yourself to fight?
[screaming]
[ITSUKI/SIEG]
'Cause this is my will.
The strength of us all!
True power!
[typing]
[ITSUKI]
Uhh...
It's done.
I finally finished it.
And there's no doubt about it.
This is my strongest,
most well-written piece
of literature to date!
[laughing]
Hell yeah!
I'm the best!
I'm so brilliant,
I scare myself sometimes!
[continues laughing]
-[chair clatters]
-[ITSUKI grunts]
Just you wait, "Mahou" fans.
I'm giving you
the greatest masterpiece yet
as thanks for... your gifts.
[ITSUKI] Check it out.
They've got 'em all on display.
I don't know about you,
but I'm always nervous
on a new release date.
It's been four whole years
since I debuted.
But this feeling
just never goes away.
Yeah, got that right.
Yes, buy it. Buy it!
You know you want to.
[inhales sharply]
Uhh...
Huh?
[groans]
-Huh?
-[HARUTO] Hmm?
-Ha!
-[grunts]
-Is that one any good?
-Yeah, I like it.
Heh! Well, clearly, that guy
has damn good taste.
Good for you.
Ha!
[grunts]
Uhh...
[ice cubes clink]
[drawn-out groan]
Come on, man.
Don't let it get to you.
My book has
the soon-to-be-an-anime bump.
Plus, it comes
with exclusive swag
depending on where you buy it.
We shouldn't be comparing
our sales
when I have
an unfair advantage.
Yeah, yeah. I know, I know.
This is nothing new.
But it's still frustrating.
A lot.
I can understand that.
Plus, this new volume is the
best work I've ever produced.
I had to suffer
to make it happen.
But I feel more accomplished
than ever before.
My efforts have never yielded
such positive results.
-I'm glad.
-Know what?
I'll even say that this is
the universe's best book.
Your "Spirit Knight
of the Distant Sea" thirteen?
It's crap next
to "Mahou Academy" five.
Best in the whole universe, eh?
You know, it's funny,
I actually find my series
to be better than yours, too.
Which means I'm the best
in the universe.
[BOTH chuckle]
Well, I'll win soon.
[HARUTO] You took the words
right out of my mouth.
Huh?
Nothing. So!
Since I'm the one
with the anime series,
food's on me today.
Are you serious?
Then I'm ordering me some cake!
[buzzing]
Uhh!
What are you worried about?
Your book came out
on time, didn't it?
Sorry, I guess
it's a force of habit.
Yeah?
[TOKI on phone]
Hey, Itsuki, can we talk?
There's something
I need to tell you.
Uh, sure, what's going on?
[TOKI] Trust me, this is
nothing to be scared of.
Congratulations.
They've decided "Mahou Academy"
will be made into a manga.
Uhh...