[ITSUKI]
Hmm.
That's not right.
I'm just trying to study
for a test,
but my school's library
is too crowded.
So, I was hoping you'd let me
study here instead.
I'm just trying to study
for a test,
but my school's library
is too crowded,
so I was really hoping
you'd let me study here instead.
Okay!
[inhales deeply]
[NAYUTA] And what are you
doing here, Myaa?
Uh!
[high-pitched voice]
I won't tell, big brother.
[normal voice]
Still not right.
[doorbell rings]
Oh. You're looking
for a place to study?
Must be tough being
a college student.
It's not easy. So, yeah.
[doorbell rings]
Hmm?
Maybe he's not home.
Hey! Turns out
the door was unlocked.
Don't just go in!
[high-pitched voice]
I'm embarrassed.
Could you turn off the lights?
[normal voice]
No. That's cute,
but I want Hilde
to be more true to herself.
I just want
to hold on to you
and never let you go!
[normal voice] No, she needs
to be even more straightforward!
[high-pitched voice] The truth
is that I love you, big brother!
-[camera shutter clicking]
-Hmm?
[laughing]
[screaming]
Well, what have we got here?
We've got nothing!
I promise I'm not insane,
I've got a good reason
to be doing this!
-I swear!
-Oh yeah, I know, don't worry.
You were just acting out a scene
in your novel. I get it.
What was that shriek?
Did you find Itsuki?
-[gasps]
-[ITSUKI screams]
Why are you naked, you pervert?
This is normal for authors!
He has to live the experience
to write about it!
If he doesn't, he can't paint
a convincing picture
for his readers!
It's research!
[MIYAKO]
So, he has to get naked?
[ITSUKI] Will you two get out
of my bathroom already?
[sighs]
Man, why can't I
figure this out?
[doorbell ringing]
What, did they forget something?
I heard you the first ti-- Huh?
So, uh, dude why are you
dressed like that?
It's nothing weird, I swear!
Uh...
[giggling]
[sighs]
Well, seeing that
just ruined my day.
What? But you're in college.
Aren't there naked guys
just walking around everywhere?
You have a warped understanding
of education.
Everything I've seen
on the internet
is all about drinking
your weight in liquor
and waking up
with a sticky face.
Not everything you see online
is true!
Fair enough. So, does that mean
you're a virgin?
Uh!
Of course I'm not a virgin.
I've had plenty of boyfriends,
so, you know...
Ah, I'm jealous.
You're so mature.
I wish I could do naughty things
with Itsuki all the time, too.
Wait, what-- Why--
The way you said that
makes it sound like
I do that stuff with him,
and you know I don't.
He's a former classmate,
and nothing more.
[NAYUTA] Oh yeah. You two went
to the same college.
How could I forget that?
[MIYAKO] He did quit
after about six months,
so I can't really blame you.
So, hey. Can you tell me
what he was like back then?
Hmm...
[yawning]
Tired today, are we?
Yeah, I got called in
in the last minute.
Barely slept at all.
I know that feeling.
My boyfriend
wouldn't let me rest
for a second last night.
Wouldn't let you rest?
Hmm?
Oh, that guy's
always off on his own,
typing up a storm.
[GIRL 2] Yeah, I think
his name's Hashima?
Kinda creepy.
[GIRL 1]
He can't have many friends.
[MIYAKO]
I got this sense that he had
something more important
than class,
goofing off, or work
that he was devoting
his time to.
Something that I didn't have.
He must've been writing
that novel every chance he got.
I swear, you could hear
the clicks of his keyboard
between every spoken word
in that room.
He'd go straight home
when class was over.
And as far as I know,
never talked to anyone.
Sounds just like him.
[laughing]
Yeah, that sucks, man.
Please don't laugh.
Sorry, sorry.
Really though, Nayu's one thing.
But for Miyako
to see you like that?
You probably ruined
the poor girl's day.
[ITSUKI grunts]
Actually, how did the two of you
become friends, anyway?
At first glance,
you don't really seem
to have anything in common.
That's a good question.
[MIYAKO]
Hey, Hashima.
What are you always typing
on that laptop of yours?
Hmm? Uhh!
What are you talking about?
It's notes and stuff.
Oh, come on,
I won't tell anyone.
I'm writing a novel.
Well, that makes sense.
I guess you want
to become a novelist
one day then, huh?
I don't want to become one.
I already am one.
Oh.
-So, I picked up your book.
-Hmm?
I read through it
yesterday after class.
You did?
Yes, but I can't say
I understood it.
Like, what exactly about kissing
his little sister
granted the guy
magic powers?
[scoffs]
Like my work is something
that a college chick
who can't keep her legs closed
could ever understand.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
I've never even had a boyfriend.
Besides, who in their right mind
would understand it?
It's crazy!
You can't honestly think
that this will connect
with readers.
Oh, I can't, can I?
You happened to have read
the second in a series.
The "Genesister of
the New World," volume two.
And it sold
one hundred thousand copies.
You're kidding me!
That garbage?
How dare you call
my masterpiece "garbage"?
Who are you to even say that?
You couldn't understand it!
"This will never connect
with your readers."
Connected with
a hundred thousand people
smarter than you.
Sorry that my work is
a little too advanced
for your reading comprehension.
Being an idiot isn't something
to be ashamed of.
But to ignore how stupid you are
and blame the world around you
because you can't
understand it is.
Why don't you just jump back
into the black hole
you crawled out of,
you dumbass tramp?
[thwack]
Uhh.
You-- You don't have
to be so mean!
You deserve
worse than that. Jerk!
[sobbing]
Wait. What? I...
I guess there might be
a slight possibility
that I went too far,
or maybe I said
something uncalled for there.
Someone posted
a really negative review
of that book the other day,
and it really pissed me off,
so I...
I, uhh...
-I guess I'm...
-[MIYAKO continues sobbing]
I'm so...
[grunts]
At least stop crying,
you streetwalker!
Will you get a clue?
I told you, I'm not easy,
and I'm not crying!
But you have tears
in your eyes--
I am not crying,
and I am not easy!
All right, all right,
have it your way.
You're not crying,
and I'm sure you're not easy.
I'm not!
[STUDENTS murmuring]
Man, this sucks so hard.
What if they think
I'm some weirdo now?
If it's any consolation,
you don't have to worry.
Everyone already thinks
you're a freak.
[chuckles]
Talk about making
a bad first impression.
After that,
we just started talking.
I would borrow books
and video games from him,
and he'd ask me about fashion.
-But...
-Hmm?
[sighs]
[phone chimes, buzzes]
Huh? Huh?
Ah!
What do you mean
you quit school?
[ITSUKI laughing]
I just realized something that
I should have known long ago!
College was nothing
but a waste of time
for a popular top-ten
genius author like myself.
Nothing but a waste of time?
[ITSUKI] I'll have way more time
to work on my novels...
[MIYAKO]
I could tell Itsuki believed
what he was saying
from the bottom of his heart.
That's why he made up
his mind so quickly.
[ITSUKI]
Hello? Miyako?
[MIYAKO]
Oh yeah? Fine.
Then you better hope
your publisher doesn't drop you!
[sighs]
This doesn't mean
you've gotten rid of me.
[NAYUTA]
Hey, Myaa?
What's the matter?
You've gone all silent on me.
Uh... it's nothing.
I was just remembering
when that idiot friend of ours
suddenly dropped out of school.
I wish I'd gone to school
with Itsuki, too.
I bet it was real fun.
You really like that
little troublemaker, don't you?
Yes. I do.
Come on.
What do you see
in that
younger-sister obsessed weirdo?
Everything.
I adore every last quirk of his.
Well, okay.
Then good luck with him.
I might as well
cheer you on, right?
Thank you very much, Myaa!
Oh, by the way.
What's up?
Would you do me a favor
and come back
to my hotel with me?
Uh!
[door closes]
[CHIHIRO]
Oh, do you have someone over?
Hey, Chihiro.
It's just me again.
Cool. What's up?
Just hanging out?
Hmm?
It's nice to meet you.
The pleasure's all mine.
[elevator bell dings]
[NAYUTA]
Here we are!
Oh! Wow.
So, is this where
you've been staying lately.
Do you pay for this
or does your publisher?
My publisher does.
So, if I don't get
a little bit of work done
while I'm here,
I'll be in trouble.
Just "a little bit" of work?
[NAYUTA] Speaking of which,
I'm going to get started.
But go ahead
and make yourself at home.
Sure.
[NAYUTA humming tune]
Whoa!
Why are you stripping?
Hmm? I can never get
any work done
if I'm not completely naked.
Okay. Whatever you say.
[keyboard clacking]
Um...
Shirakawa, tell me right now
if you like Itsuki.
Excuse me?
That came out of nowhere.
And he's just a friend
from school, that's all.
Well, for your information,
I do like him.
Itsuki is everything to me.
What do you see in that dumb,
little-sister obsessed freak?
The man you see as a freak
saved me.
That's what I see in him.
[horns honking]
Uh!
I'm so sorry I couldn't have
been there for you
when you needed someone!
I would have kicked
every one of their asses
for treating you that way!
[MIYAKO sobbing]
[NAYUTA]
Thank you.
[laughs]
[CHIHIRO]
Here you go.
Sweet.
Thanks for the food.
Oh, one sec.
What?
Throw up a peace sign
over your rice.
Hmm? Like this?
[camera shutter clicking]
Awesome.
Okay, what was that all about?
Hmm? Trying to appeal
to the ladies.
I'm not sure I follow.
What do you mean?
So, lately,
I've been showing my face
in magazines and on streams.
If you're at all good-looking,
people jump to conclusions
and think you're trying
to seduce voice actors
to be in your show.
So, I'm building an image of me
hanging out with guys
more than girls.
That way everyone feels safe.
Plus, I'll get more lady fans
who are into that kind thing.
Best of both worlds, am I right?
Oh.
[ITSUKI] Don't call yourself
good-looking, dude.
And wait a sec.
You're dragging me
into this, too!
Couldn't you have warned me
about your master plan?
Don't worry, man.
Thank me later.
Are you kidding me?
If I'm gonna look gay,
I don't want it to be with you!
Look at the bright side,
you'll be getting a whole new
league of passionate fans.
No, thanks!
Besides, I wouldn't want
my books to sell
just because
of the person I am.
[HARUTO chuckles]
[HARUTO] You get serious
about the weirdest stuff.
Hey, Myaa?
What's up?
Do you need something?
Let me fondle
your boobs real quick.
W-- And why should I
let you do that?
I'm in the middle of writing
a scene about squeezing tatas.
And I gotta live it
to write about it.
May I remind you that you have
perfectly good breasts
of your own to grab?
Yes, but the cup size
of the character in question
is just about
the same as yours.
Did you think that
that would convince me?
[NAYUTA]
Please!
I need to do this to paint
a vivid, realistic picture!
[MIYAKO] So that naked stunt
really was for work.
[sighs]
Fine. Let's just
get this over with.
Oh, I need them bare,
if you would.
And you conveniently forgot
to mention that until right now?
What if I said "pretty please"?
With sugar on top?
The next time I need a favor,
you had better say yes!
You're the best, Myaa!
[giggles]
[MIYAKO]
Time to take this off.
You sure put on
a good show, hot stuff.
J-- Just for
a few seconds, okay.
And don't be too rough
on them either.
I humbly thank you
for this treat.
[moans]
Give it up!
I said I only wanna flirt
with little sisters, man!
And mark my words,
one day I shall create
the ultimate little sister!
I don't even know how to respond
to that at this point.
Like, I actually have
a little sister.
And let me tell you, they're not
as great as you make them seem.
All she does is complain
about every little thing I do.
Plus, she'll smack me
for nothing
and tell me my books
are gross or boring.
Then she gets on my case
about interviews,
because they're "inconvenient."
-It's depressing.
-Oh, whatever!
Don't compare
that piece of trash
in little sisters' clothing
to my little sister!
Whoa, damn, dude!
She may not be perfect,
but she's not that bad!
I'll have you know,
she used to be
as cute as a button
when she was little!
And the last time I got sick,
she even went out and bought
some gelatin for me.
Also, you don't even have
a little sister!
Yes, I do.
Huh?
For she lives in my heart!
-Okay.
-[CHIHIRO sighs]
I'm done.
[MIYAKO giggles]
Interesting.
All right, I think
I've got my fill.
I should be able to write
a good scene now.
Good.
Glad I could be of assistance.
Now it's time to get
on that ass, girl!
[MIYAKO]
What?
[ITSUKI groans]
Chihiro.
Water.
Chihiro went home
a long time ago.
[sighs, groans]
Yo. Itsuki.
I don't wanna go.
Do you remember your own name?
You can't make... me.
[HARUTO]
And what's your address?
Where do you live?
Get outta here.
[chuckles]
All right.
[exhales sharply]
-[keyboard clacking]
-Hmm?
[MIYAKO] Itsuki and Nayu
are both working hard.
But what am I doing?
[yawns]
That's enough progress
for one sitting!
Glad it went smoothly.
[NAYUTA] It only went
so smooth because of you.
Thanks again for helping out
with my research.
Uh...
[chuckles]
You're welcome, I guess.
Well, it's getting late, so I
think I'm gonna head out now.
[ITSUKI] Besides,
I wouldn't want my books to sell
just because
of the person I am.
[mouse wheel clicking]
Just you watch.
[HARUTO] While you geniuses
are sitting at a standstill,
I'm going
to keep moving forward.
[door closes]
[HARUTO]
I'm home.
You're late again, big bro!
So?
Don't "so?" me.
How many times
do I have to tell you
to let me know
if you're going to be late?
Oh. Yeah, I forgot.
[grunts]
You never forget to make
your creepy social media posts.
It's part of my work.
I'm building a persona!
That's lame. Who would want
to read something like that?
There's plenty of female fans
who are into that kind of thing.
Okay, sure,
but aren't your books marketed
towards virgin guys?
What are you gonna do
with some more female fans?
So what? Because
it's marketed towards guys,
I'm not allowed to hear some
opinions from the other gender?
-[GIRL grunts]
-[HARUTO groans]
You're such a jerk!
And a pervert!
Go play one
of your raunchy games!
So, mind if I ask
how Kani's manuscript
is comin' along?
It's as perfect as usual.
I'm her editor, and I can't find
a single thing wrong.
Must be nice working
with someone that easy.
It would be, if she could just
figure out what a deadline is.
How's our favorite
little sister-obsessed author?
Well, he's a handful,
like always.
Which reminds me,
I should call him.
-[phone buzzes]
-[ITSUKI snoring]
[ITSUKI] No matter
what you want in life,
there's always someone else
who already has it.
And unfortunately,
it usually means a whole lot
less to that someone.
It's nothing short of a miracle
when you do actually have
what you want.
And you can blame
the absence of this miracle
for most comedies.
And tragedies.
It may not be fair...
but that's just how
the world works.
-[phone buzzing]
-[ITSUKI snoring]
Yup?
[TOKI on phone]
Itsuki,
how's the progress
on your manuscript?
Uh, it's coming along fine.
[TOKI]
That better be the truth.
Yeah.
[ITSUKI grunts]
[groans loudly]
[ITSUKI]
I want a little sister!
-[water splashing]
-[CHIHIRO] Uh...
[giggles]