- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ANYWAY, YOU CAN'T
GO AFTER YUJI.
- SURE I CAN.
YOU ARE BEING COMPLETELY
UNFAIR ABOUT THIS.
BUT I'M GONNA TELL
SAKAI THAT I LOVE HIM,
AND YOU'LL BE OUT
OF THE PICTURE.
- IT IS NOT UNFAIR. YOU CAN'T GO
AFTER HIM, 'CAUSE YUJI IS MY...
YUJI IS MY WHAT?
BELIEVE ME, IT'S BETTER FOR
YUJI TO BE WITH ME THAN YOU.
- THAT IS NOT TRUE. SAKAI SHOULD
BE THE ONE TO DECIDE THAT.
- BUT YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT YUJI.
- I'LL GET TO KNOW HIM.
- YOU CAN'T.
- WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE I SAY SO.
- I SAID WHAT I HAD TO SAY.
- FORGET IT.
I WON'T LOSE TO YOU.
- THERE'S NO DOUBT,
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
IS INSIDE THAT MYSTES.
- ( birds chirping )
- HERE, THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
- ( sighs ) IS ANYTHING
THE MATTER, SHANA?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- DON'T TAKE THIS WRONG,
BUT SOMETIMES...
IT KINDA SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE
IRRITATED ABOUT SOMETHING.
- SHUT UP, SHUT UP, SHUT UP.
YOU'RE GOING TO RUIN
THE TASTE FOR ME.
NO WAY, I'M NOT GOING
TO LOSE TO HER.
Mmm, mmm.
- THAT'S NOT THE WAY YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO EAT MELON BREAD.
- Hmm?
- LIKE THIS. FIRST YOU
BITE OFF THE CRISPY BUN.
AND THEN YOU SAVOR THE
SPONGY SOFT FILLING.
ANOTHER BITE OF THE CRISPY PART,
FOLLOWED BY MORE SPONGY FILLING.
THIS ALLOWS YOU TO BALANCE BOTH
TEXTURES EQUALLY. YOU GOT IT?
- UH, YEAH, SURE.
- GOOD.
WHAT IS THIS SPICE
THEY'VE ADDED?
THIS SHOP HAS NO RESPECT
FOR THE NATURAL TASTE
OF REAL MELON BREAD.
- ( laughs )
YOU REALLY LOVE IT, DON'T YOU?
- HUH?
- WHEN I THINK OF YOU, I ALWAYS
THINK ABOUT HOW MUCH
YOU LOVE MELON BREAD.
- LOVE?
- YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW A WHOLE LOT
ABOUT SHANA,
BUT I DO KNOW TWO THINGS
FOR CERTAIN,
THAT SHE'S A FLAME HAZE,
AND THAT SHE SURE
LOVES MELON BREAD.
THERE'S NO DOUBT THOSE
TWO THINGS ARE VERY
IMPORTANT TO WHO SHE IS.
AND I'M ALSO SURE THERE'S
A PRETTY GOOD REASON
WHY SHE LOVES
THOSE BUNS SO MUCH.
- ( Shana grunting )
- ( bell tolling )
- ( grunting )
- Wirhelmina: AND THAT ABOUT
SUMS IT UP, FLAME OF HEAVEN.
- Alastor: WELL, WHAT
DO YOU THINK?
- SHE IS MOST SUITABLE INDEED.
SHE EXCELS AT BOTH HER STUDIES
AND THE MARTIAL ARTS.
SHE QUICKLY APPLIES WHAT SHE
LEARNS, KNOWS HER LIMITATIONS,
AND HAS A MERCILESS WORK ETHIC.
- ( grunts )
- INDEED IT'S RARE TO FIND SUCH
SELF-RESPECT
COMBINED WITH A NATURAL
ABILITY TO FIGHT.
IT'S POINTLESS TO EVEN COMPARE
HER TO THE OTHERS WE'VE SEEN.
SHE IS INDEED AN INDIVIDUAL
OF EXCEPTIONAL TALENT.
- Alastor: UNEXPECTED RESULTS
FROM A GIRL
WE ENCOUNTERED
BY HAPPENSTANCE.
- Wirhelmina: THE UNFORTUNATE
INCIDENTS WERE A COINCIDENCE,
AS WAS MY APPEARANCE
ON THE SCENE.
LIKEWISE MY BRINGING HER HERE,
TO THE PALACE OF HEAVEN'S ROAD.
- Alastor: HMM, WHAT IS IT?
YOU SEEM UNEASY ABOUT SOMETHING.
- Wirhelmina: YOU MUST BE
AWARE OF THIS, INDEED AS I AM,
BUT I GET THE FEELING
SHE HAS ANOTHER SIDE,
A SIDE SHE'S NOT SHOWING US.
I FEEL INDEED SHE IS KEEPING
A SECRET TO HERSELF,
ONE THAT SHE HAS DECIDED
NOT TO REVEAL TO US.
SOMETHING IN THE DARKEST
CORNERS OF HER HEART,
A MYSTERY THAT NO ONE
MUST KNOW ABOUT.
- Alastor: YOU'RE RIGHT, BUT YOU
COULD SAY THE SAME THING
FOR EVERY ONE OF US.
- YES.
- ( screams )
- ( clicking )
- Wirhelmina: INDEED ALL THIS
TIME AND YOU STILL HAVEN'T
LANDED A BLOW ON SHIRO.
- HELLO, WIRHELMINA.
- I GUESS YOU'RE BACK
FROM SHOPPING.
- YES.
- OH, DID YOU BRING
ME A TREAT AGAIN?
- ( chuckles )
- AW...
- INDEED YOUR FAULT, NOT HIS,
THAT IT WAS RUINED.
- I CAN'T FIGHT IN
THIS STUPID OUTFIT.
THE SKIRT IS TOO LONG, IT KEEPS
GETTING IN MY WAY WHEN I KICK.
I CAN'T KEEP UP WITH SHIRO
WEARING THIS.
- IN THE WORLD THAT LIES OUTSIDE
THE PALACE OF HEAVEN'S ROAD,
THAT IS THE ATTIRE OF MANY
WARRIORS
OF OUTSTANDING
ABILITY AND SKILL.
- YEAH, BUT...
- INDEED I HAVE PERSONALLY
WITNESSED MANY INDIVIDUALS
MOVING AND FIGHTING
AT TOP SPEED
IN JUST SUCH AN OUTFIT,
THOUGH THEY HAVE FEWER
PROBLEMS THAN YOU DO.
- ( grunts )
- ( groans )
- YOU'RE NOT BEING
FAIR, WIRHELMINA.
- FAIR HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH IT. I'M HERE TO JUDGE YOU.
- CRIMSON DENIZENS
THAT EAT PEOPLE?
AND THE FLAME HAZES
WHO BATTLE THEM?
IS THE OUTSIDE WORLD
REALLY LIKE THAT?
- ( bell tolling )
- ( clicks )
- THIS TIME FOR SURE.
- I TOLD YOU, I'M OKAY.
- SO WHERE DOES IT
HURT THE MOST?
- MY RIBS, ON THE RIGHT.
- DO YOU NEED TREATMENT?
- NO THANKS.
- OW!
- THAT LOOKS FAIRLY
PAINFUL TO ME.
- ANYONE WOULD JUMP
IN THE AIR IF YOU POKED THEM
IN THE SIDE LIKE THAT.
- THAT BEHAVIOR IS
QUITE RUDE INDEED.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT AND REST EASY.
THERE IS PLENTY OF TIME
BEFORE IT HAPPENS.
- I CAN'T SLEEP, ALASTOR.
COULD YOU TELL ME
MY FAVORITE STORY AGAIN?
THE FLAME-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
- ( humming )
- ARE YOU GOING SHOPPING TODAY?
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
I'LL BE BACK THIS EVENING.
YOUR LUNCH IS IN
THE MICROWAVE, INDEED.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- Hmm.
- THE ONLY THING LEFT
TO PICK UP...
IS INDEED ONE OF
THOSE BUNS SHE LIKES.
- Tiamat: UNRESTRICTED METHOD.
- ANALYSIS CONFIRMED.
BUT I'M ONLY PICKING UP
AN EXTREMELY WEAK ENTITY NEARBY.
- BE ALERT.
- ACKNOWLEDGED.
I'VE BEEN EXTRA CAUTIOUS
LATELY INDEED.
- ( people murmuring )
- I CONCLUDE THAT NOTHING HAS
CHANGED AND IT'S SAFE
TO MAKE THE ASSUMPTION
THAT OUR LOCATION
IS STILL UNKNOWN TO THOSE
WHO MIGHT BE HUNTING US.
- CARELESSNESS IS YOUR ENEMY.
- I UNDERSTAND.
HOWEVER, THE PALACE OF
HEAVEN'S ROAD IS UNDETECTABLE.
INDEED, NOT EVEN A MASTER OF
UNRESTRICTED METHODS
COULD FIND IT.
- ( Vine laughing )
PUTTING A NET HERE
WASN'T A BAD IDEA.
PALACE OF HEAVEN'S ROAD,
HERE I COME.
YOU! THOUSAND ORDINANCES.
- I NEVER EXPECTED TO SEE YOU
IN ASIA, THOUSAND ORDINANCES.
- IT'S NOT THAT UNUSUAL,
CONSIDERING I'VE BEEN SENT HERE
BY A LEADER OF THE BALL MASQUE,
BEL PEOL TO BE SPECIFIC.
- IS THERE AN
OPERATION UNDERWAY?
- EVEN SOMEONE LIKE YOU MUST
KNOW OF OUR MANY BROTHERS
WHO HAVE FALLEN AS OF LATE,
ONE AFTER THE OTHER.
- YES, THERE'S A POWERFUL
FLAME HAZE SOMEWHERE OUT THERE.
- MANY OF OUR FALLEN BROTHERS
WERE VERY SKILLFUL,
WHICH MEANS OUR ENEMY IS TRULY
A FORCE TO BE RECKONED WITH.
ANY INFORMATION?
- I'M SO CLOSE TO FINDING THE
PALACE OF HEAVEN'S ROAD.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET
HIM CLAIM THE GLORY
AFTER ALL MY HARD WORK.
- YOU WORM, YOU KNOW SOMETHING.
- UH, YES. AN ENEMY,
JUST A MOMENT AGO.
- OH? AND WHAT KIND
OF ENEMY DID YOU FIND?
- THERE'S NO DOUBT. I FOUND
A FLAME HAZE DOWN THERE.
WE COULD GET INFORMATION ON
YOUR QUARRY BY INTERROGATING IT.
- VERY WELL. HOWEVER POWERFUL
THIS ENEMY MIGHT BE,
I WILL TRACK IT DOWN
AND CRUSH IT.
- EXCELLENT. I AM TRULY
GRATEFUL FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE.
I JUST HOPE HE DOESN'T KILL
THE FLAME HAZE
BEFORE IT CAN LEAD
ME TO THE PALACE.
- ( microwave bell dings )
- HOW CAN I BEAT SHIRO? HMM.
- ( screams )
- HUH?
- ( chuckles ) THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE LAST.
SHIRO TAUGHT ME THAT ONE OF
THE BASIC RULES
IS TO CATCH YOUR
OPPONENT OFF GUARD.
- ( engine revving )
- Bel Peol: BIND THE
DRIFTING EYE. HELP ME.
AVENGE THE LOSS
OF YOUR BROTHERS.
THE TOOLS OF DESTRUCTION, THE
PATHETIC FLAME HAZES MUST PAY.
SLAUGHTER THEM.
SLAUGHTER THEM ALL.
- LADY BEL PEOL, YOUR PATIENCE
IS ABOUT TO BE REWARDED.
I AM ON THE VERGE
OF ACCOMPLISHING
SOMETHING MAGNIFICENT.
A TRULY MOMENTOUS
EVENT IS AT HAND.
- Wirhelmina: WHICH ONE? OH.
Mmm...
MAYBE...
OH, NO.
INDEED I SHOULDN'T SPOIL HER,
BUT SHE'S... NO.
OH, MAYBE JUST ONE.
- Tiamat: INCOMING.
- ROGER THAT. CONFIRMED.
- LEAVE NOW.
- ABANDONING BAGGAGE.
PREPARE FOR IMMEDIATE
EXIT OF AREA.
- Orgon: I DON'T BELIEVE
WE'VE EVER MET, FLAME HAZE.
- ORGON,
THE THOUSAND ORDINANCES.
- Tiamat: CORRECT.
- WHAT'S WRONG? WHY AREN'T YOU
CHANGING TO PREPARE FOR BATTLE?
COULD IT BE YOU'RE A NOVICE?
NEWLY CONTRACTED
AND UNSURE OF YOUR POWERS?
HMM, THAT'S WHAT
I GET FOR LISTENING
TO A LIGHTWEIGHT LIKE VINE.
WELL, NOW THAT I'M HERE, I'LL
FIND OUT WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF.
FIRST, HAVE A TASTE OF HOGIER.
NEXT, BEHOLD THE POWER
OF LA HIRE.
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING TO REVEAL
YOUR TRUE APPEARANCE,
THEN THERE'S NO NEED
FOR ME TO EMPLOY
THE REMAINDER OF MY FOUR CARDS.
- AH YES, THAT'S THOUSAND
ORDINANCE'S POWER, LEGION.
- ( bell tolling )
- I GOT HIM.
UH, OKAY, I BET
THAT WAS A SURPRISE.
- ( screams in pain )
- ( screaming )
- ( screeches )
- HUH?
- WHAT? WHAT IS THAT?
- ( gasps )
I, I FOUND IT.
THE PALACE OF HEAVEN'S ROAD.
- WE HAVE A REAL
EMERGENCY INDEED.
- THIS IS FANTASTIC. THE WORLD
HAS STARTED TO TURN IN MY FAVOR.
- MIGHTY WARRIOR,
I AM HERE TO FIGHT YOU.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE CRIMSON DENIZENS
ATTACK, JOINED BY TENMOKUIKKO,
THE MOST POWERFUL MYSTES OF ALL.
AS THE PALACE SHAKES,
A YOUNG GIRL BECOMES
A FLAME HAZE.
NEXT EPISODE,
"THE DAY THE FLAME WAS BORN."