- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE CRIMSON
WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Shana: YUJI, SEND ME YOUR
STRENGTH, LITTLE BY LITTLE.
- OKAY.
- HERE I GO.
- Alastor: HMM, IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S GETTING EASIER FOR YOU
TO FIND YOUR WINGS.
- SEEMS THAT WAY.
HA!
- ( beeping )
- SHANA, IT'S ALMOST TIME.
- IS IT?
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S
ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
- 12:00.
MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
I'M GLAD ALL MY ENERGY COMES
BACK, BUT IT SURE FEELS STRANGE.
- BETTER GET USED TO IT.
- YEAH, I GUESS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'M A LITTLE HUNGRY.
- HUH?
- WANNA COME INSIDE FOR A SNACK?
- WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?
- I THINK IT'S A RERUN
OF A DRAMA.
- DRAMA?
YOU MEAN IT'S NOT EVEN REAL?
- YEAH.  SHOULD I TURN IT OFF?
SAY THE WORD.
- IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
TO ME.
- RIE!
- OW!
- THAT MUST'VE HURT.
- SO WHY DID SHE HIT HIM ANYWAY?
- WELL, I GUESS HIS KISS
TOOK HER BY SURPRISE.
PRETTY NATURAL REACTION.
- JUST BECAUSE OF THAT.
- JUST BECAUSE--
- YOU DON'T FIND IT STRANGE?
- TIRIEL, EVERYONE'S
LOOKING AT US.
THEY'RE STARTING TO SCARE ME.
- CALM YOURSELF.
THERE'S NOTHING TO FEAR.
- Man: THAT'S DISGUSTING.
- IT'S YOUR BEHAVIOR
AS WELL AS YOUR OUTFITS
THAT ARE ATTRACTING
ALL THE ATTENTION.
- WHY?  THERE'S NOTHING
SHAMEFUL ABOUT A PAIR
OF MAGNIFICENT FLOWERS IN BLOOM.
- ( clears throat )
- DON'T FORGET IT'S MY CRADLE
GARDEN THAT IS PROTECTING YOU.
I DON'T APPRECIATE
YOUR FLIPPANT COMMENT.
- OH, TIRIEL,
CAN I EAT THEM UP?
- YES, OF COURSE YOU CAN,
DEAR BROTHER,
BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL AFTER I'M FINISHED.
- SO WHAT METHOD IS THAT?
- WE'RE GETTING CLOSE TO WHAT
MY BROTHER IS LOOKING FOR.
I'M GETTING SOMETHING READY.
IT WOULD BE A SHAME
IF WE FOUND IT,
ONLY TO HAVE SOMEONE ELSE WALK
AWAY WITH IT, DON'T YOU THINK?
- YOU'RE GONNA TRAP IT SO NO ONE
WILL BE ABLE TO TAKE IT AWAY.
INSIDE OUR CRADLE!
- THERE WE GO.
HELP YOURSELF TO AS MANY
AS YOU LIKE, DEAR BROTHER.
EXCEPT FOR THIS ONE.
- MMM!  IT'S TIME TO EAT!
- TELL ME, HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF SOMETHING CALLED AN ORGEL?
- AN ORGEL YOU SAY.
THAT'S SOME KIND OF MUSIC BOX.
- THAT'S RIGHT.  I BELIEVE
THAT'S THE COMMON NAME,
BUT I PREFER THE TERM "ORGEL,"
BECAUSE IT JUST SOUNDS
SO MUCH MORE ELEGANT.
- Sydonay: YOU'RE GOING TO
USE THAT TREASURE,
AND THE UNRESTRICTED METHOD
TO CREATE THE ENCLOSURE.
- IT HAS SUCH A BEAUTIFUL TONE.
- ( whistle blows )
- ( Yuji grunts )
MAN, DODGEBALL AT OUR AGE?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, SAKAI?
- YEAH, I'M JUST FINE.
- BOO-YAH!
( gasps ) OH!
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- TANAKA!
- IT'S COMING DOWN
IN BUCKETS OUT THERE.
- BUT I'M GLAD THE GAME
WAS CANCELLED.
THE WAY THINGS WERE GOING,
SOMEONE MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN HURT.
REALLY HURT.
- BIG SISTER.
- BIG SISTER?  WHO IS THAT?
- HE WAS REALLY KNOCKED
FOR A LOOP.
LISTEN, SAKAI.
- HMM?
- I WANNA ASK YOU ABOUT HIRAI.
- OKAY, WHAT DO YOU WANNA KNOW?
- YOU GUYS COME TO SCHOOL
TOGETHER PRETTY OFTEN.
LET'S SEE, IS THERE ANYTHING
BETWEEN YOU TWO?
- NO, NO,
THERE'S NOTHING GOING ON.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- Girl #1:
THEY SAY JUST ONE KISS.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU GIVE AWAY
LIKE IT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
-  Girl #2: I TOTALLY KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
YOU LET THEM KISS YOU,
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
THEY'VE GONE TOO FAR.
- Girl #1: WHAT?
- Girl #2:
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
IT'S LIKE, A KISS IS PRECIOUS.
- Girl #1: HUH?
OH, THAT'S WHAT YOU MEANT.
- Girl #2:
IT'S HARD TO KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- Girl #1: SURE, IT IS.
- HUH?
A KISS.
YUJI HAD A STRANGE REACTION WHEN
WE TALKED ABOUT THAT YESTERDAY.
EVERYTHING I'VE READ HERE MAKES
IT SOUND STRAIGHTFORWARD.
( sighs ) BUT STILL.
- Yuji: AH, HERE YOU ARE.
- SO YOU DOING SOME RESEARCH?
- YEAH, SORT OF.
- ON WHAT?
- STUFF, YOU KNOW,
NOTHING THAT IMPORTANT.
- DON'T LOOK SO WORRIED,
YOSHIDA.
- IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK IT IS.
- IT ISN'T?
- IT'S LIKE WHAT
I WAS TELLING YOU BEFORE.
HIRAI AND SAKAI ARE
JUST GOOD FRIENDS.
THEY'RE NOT IN LOVE
WITH EACH OTHER.
SO HANG IN THERE.
- OKAY.
BIG SISTER, WE'RE HOME!
SO HOW YOU FEELING TODAY?
- WOULD YOU TWO BE QUIET?
IT FEELS LIKE MY HEAD
IS SPLITTING WIDE OPEN.
- YO, EITA, WHAT'S WITH
THE WAR WOUND ON YOUR CHIN?
- THIS?  OH, I TOOK A BALL
IN THE FACE TODAY.
- KEISAKU, EITA,
I THINK I'M GROWING TIRED
OF BOOZE.
- OH.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"WHAT DO YOU MEAN?"
- I'M WONDERING, WHAT IS
THE REAL MEANING OF A KISS?
- OH, WHY DO YOU WANNA KNOW
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- JUST BECAUSE.
- A SIMPLE QUESTION, BUT IT'S
A DIFFICULT ONE TO ANSWER.
YOU SAID YOU DID
SOME RESEARCH?
- I LOOKED THROUGH A BUNCH
OF LIBRARY BOOKS,
BUT I DIDN'T FIND ANYTHING
THAT I DON'T ALREADY KNOW.
I'M AWARE OF WHAT'S INVOLVED,
AND I'VE SEEN PEOPLE KISSING,
BUT IT'S LIKE--
- LIKE WHAT?
- I GET THE FEELING THAT
THE MEANING I ATTACH TO A KISS
AND THE MEANING EVERYONE ELSE
HAS ARE TWO DIFFERENT THINGS.
I THOUGHT YOU COULD TELL ME
WHAT A KISS IS REALLY ABOUT.
- HAVE YOU READ NOVELS
OR MAGAZINES ABOUT IT?
- I HAVE, BUT ALASTOR
SAID THOSE THINGS ARE USELESS
BECAUSE ANYTHING WRITTEN DOWN
HAS A PERSONAL OPINION IN IT,
AND IT WON'T BE VERY ANALYTICAL
OR LOGICAL.
- ALASTOR IS YOUR GUARDIAN,
RIGHT?
HE'S THE ONE WHO LIVES
A LONG WAY AWAY.
HE SOUNDS VERY INSIGHTFUL.
- OH, HE IS.
- HOWEVER,
IT'S NOT QUITE SO SIMPLE.
- OH.
- HOWEVER, SHANA-CHAN,
SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
IT'S NATURAL FOR YOU
TO HAVE QUESTIONS ABOUT IT.
- I GUESS SO.
- IF YOU WANT ACCURATE
INFORMATION AND THEORIES,
BOOKS ARE THE BEST THINGS
TO START WITH.
BUT WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
HAS VERY LITTLE TO DO
WITH COLD FACTS AND FIGURES.
IN OTHER WORDS, THIS IS
SOMETHING WITH NO RIGHT ANSWER.
IT HAS TO DO WITH THE HEART
AND EMOTIONS.
- THE HEART AND EMOTIONS?
- YOU DO UNDERSTAND THAT
PHYSICAL CONTACT
BETWEEN TWO PEOPLE IS USUALLY
A SIGN OF AFFECTION, RIGHT?
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT A KISS IS.
KIND OF LIKE WHEN PEOPLE SHAKE
HANDS OR HUG EACH OTHER.
EVERYONE DOES IT.
- HMM, WELL, THAT'S TRUE,
BUT LET'S TAKE ALASTOR.
YOU WOULDN'T MIND GIVING HIM
A LITTLE KISS, RIGHT?
WOULD YOU GIVE YU-CHAN A KISS?
- BUT-- BUT HE'S--
- WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
IT LIKE THAT,
IT'S UNCOMFORTABLE ISN'T IT?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S THE ESSENCE
OF WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY.
- AND REMEMBER THAT A HARMLESS
PECK ON THE CHEEK
IS A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT THING
FROM TWO PEOPLE
KISSING EACH OTHER
ON THE LIPS.
- A KISS ON THE LIPS?
FROM YUJI?
NO, I DON'T EVER
WANNA DO THAT.
- THAT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
- CHIGUSA--
- NO ONE SAYS YOU HAVE TO.
IN FACT, IT'S PROBABLY NOT
SOMETHING YOU SHOULD BE DOING
- WITH ALASTOR, EITHER.
- ( gasps )
- SHANA-CHAN, THIS IS HOW
I FEEL ABOUT A KISS.
IF IT'S ON THE LIPS,
THEN IT'S LIKE A PERSONAL OATH.
- AN OATH?
- YES, IT MEANS THE TWO
OF YOU WANT TO BE CLOSER,
THAT YOU'RE WILLING
TO LET THE OTHER PERSON
TAKE CARE OF YOU.
- SO THAT'S IT.
- THAT'S ENOUGH FOR TONIGHT.
- ( sighs )
I AM A LITTLE TIRED.
SHANA, I'VE BEEN WONDERING.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- MY ENERGY MAKES A COMPLETE
RECOVERY EVERY NIGHT,
BECAUSE OF THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD TREASURE.
- YEAH, SO?
- DOES THAT MEAN
I'M GOING TO LIVE FOREVER?
- THAT'S SOMETHING YOU'LL HAVE
TO FIND OUT FOR YOURSELF.
IT'LL BE A WHILE BEFORE
YOU KNOW FOR CERTAIN.
- I SEE.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I WAS WONDERING IF THIS MEANS
THAT NOW WE'RE ALWAYS
GOING TO BE TOGETHER.
- Alastor: SHANA.
- WHAT?
- I HAVE A FAVOR TO ASK OF YOU.
OF BOTH OF YOU.
- SO IS THIS OKAY, ALASTOR?
- HMM.
- CHIGUSA,
CAN I USE YOUR PHONE?
- GO AHEAD, BUT, SHANA-CHAN,
IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR SCHOOL.
- RIGHT.
- ( cellphone rings )
- HELLO.
- HMM, ALL RIGHT,
LET'S BEGIN.
- CHIGUSA.
- FOR ME?
- HELLO, YOU WANTED
TO TALK TO ME?
- HELLO.
- YES.
- MADAME, IT IS A GREAT PLEASURE
TO FINALLY BE ABLE
TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
MY NAME IS ALASTOR.
- AH, SO THIS
IS THE FAMOUS MR. ALASTOR.
YUKARI'S TOLD ME ALL ABOUT YOU.
SHE SPEAKS VERY HIGHLY OF YOU.
I'M YUJI'S MOTHER, BUT YOU CAN
CALL ME CHIGUSA.  EVERYONE DOES.
- I WANT
TO TAKE THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO THANK YOU
FOR LOOKING OUT FOR HER.
- OH, NO, I HAVEN'T
DONE THAT MUCH.
PLEASE DON'T THINK I'M BEING
TOO FORWARD,
BUT MAY I ASK WHY YOU WANTED
TO SPEAK TO ME?
I'M SURE THIS HAS SOMETHING
TO DO WITH YUKARI HIRAI.
- INDEED IT DOES.
AND PLEASE FEEL FREE
TO CALL HER SHANA.
THAT'S THE NAME I USE
WHEN ADDRESSING HER.
- AH, SO IT'S A PERSONAL
NICKNAME THAT YOU GAVE HER.
- WELL, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- ABOUT THE REASON
FOR MY TELEPHONE CALL.
- YES.
- IT HAS TO DO
WITH WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY.
- YESTERDAY?
HUH?
- COULD YOU HOLD ON
A MOMENT PLEASE?
- YU-CHAN, SHANA-CHAN, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- Both: WE'RE GOING NOW.
- GO, I'LL SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
HURRY UP, GET GOING.
I'M SORRY
TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
- I AM NOT DISPUTING YOUR
KNOWLEDGE WHEN IT COMES
TO RELATIONSHIPS, HOWEVER,
I MUST ASK THAT YOU REFRAIN
FROM CONVERSATIONS
OF THAT NATURE.
- OH, I SEE.
THEN SHE MUST HAVE TALKED
TO YOU ABOUT IT.
- NO, MORE LIKE I TEASED
IT OUT OF HER.
- WELL, WHAT REALLY MATTERS IS
THAT SHANA WAS STILL WILLING
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
IT SHOWS HOW MUCH SHE TRUSTS YOU
AND RESPECTS YOUR OPINION.
- HMM.
- IT'S CLEAR YOU CARE FOR HER.
YOU'VE DONE A WONDERFUL
JOB RAISING HER.
SHE'S A LOVELY YOUNG GIRL
WITH A GOOD HEART.
- THAT SHE IS, AND THAT'S
PRECISELY WHY I MUST ASK YOU
TO DESIST FROM
ANY FURTHER DISCUSSIONS
THAT COULD STIMULATE IMPROPER
THOUGHTS
CONCERNING YOUR SON YUJI.
- HMM.  YES, I UNDERSTAND
YOUR CONCERN.
- YOU ARE AN ASTUTE WOMAN,
MADAME.
I'M SURE YOU CAN IMAGINE EXACTLY
WHAT I'M WORRIED ABOUT HERE.
- YES, BUT--
- HMM?
- FOR SHANA-CHAN'S SAKE,
MAY I HAVE PERMISSION TO TALK
TO HER ABOUT THIS SUBJECT
SOME TIME IN THE FUTURE?
- OKAY.
- WITH YOUR GUIDANCE,
SHE'S BECOME A PROUD, STRONG
AND GOOD-HEARTED YOUNG WOMAN,
BUT LET'S NOT KID OURSELVES.
SHE'S STILL VERY YOUNG
AND INSECURE ABOUT SOME THINGS.
- HMM, PLEASE CONTINUE.
- WELL, FORGIVE ME,
BUT I HAVE TO BE FRANK.
I DON'T THINK SHE UNDERSTANDS
FEELINGS VERY WELL,
AND SHE'S EXTREMELY VULNERABLE
WHEN IT COMES
TO MATTERS OF THE HEART.
IMAGINE A YOUNG MAN,
SOMEONE AGGRESSIVE
OR EVEN MY OWN SON YUJI.
SHE'S JUST SO NAIVE.
I DON'T THINK SHE COULD RESIST.
YESTERDAY SHE SAID SOME THINGS
THAT WORRIED ME.
THAT'S WHY I HAD
TO TALK WITH HER.
- DON'T YOU THINK IT'S STILL TOO
EARLY FOR THESE KINDS OF TALKS?
I'D ALWAYS PLANNED TO GRADUALLY
INTRODUCE THESE THINGS
OVER A NUMBER OF YEARS
IN RESPONSE TO NEW
AND INTERESTING EXPERIENCES
IN HER LIFE.
- PROBLEMS DON'T ARISE WHEN WE'D
LIKE THEM TO, NOW DO THEY?
- INDEED THEY DO NOT.
- THEREFORE, THERE ARE
SOME THINGS THAT CHILDREN
ARE NEVER TOO YOUNG TO LEARN,
ESPECIALLY IF IT'S SOMETHING
THAT THEY HAVE TO KNOW.
IT'S FOR HER OWN SAKE.
BESIDES, GIRLS CAN
BE QUITE PRECOCIOUS.
THEY'RE MORE MATURE
THAN THEY APPEAR.
- MADAME.
- YES.
- PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO RETRACT MY EARLIER REMARKS.
THEY WERE ILL-INFORMED.
- WELL, I HOPE YOU'LL FORGIVE ME
FOR HAVING BEEN SO DIRECT,
BUT I WOULDN'T WORRY
ABOUT SHANA-CHAN.
WITH THE PROPER CARE
AND GUIDANCE,
SHE'LL BE READY
FOR WHATEVER HAPPENS.
SHE CAN FIND THE RIGHT ANSWERS
IN HER OWN WAY,
AND YOU TRUST HER
IN THAT REGARD, DON'T YOU?
- OF COURSE I DO.
- OH, BROTHER.
HUH?
- Sorath:
IT'S CLOSE. REALLY CLOSE.
- WHAT IS IT, SYDONAY?
YOU SEEM TO BE LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING.  COULD IT BE--
- I'M ALWAYS AMAZED
AT HOW SORATH CAN SMELL
THE THINGS THAT HE WANTS.
THIS UNPLEASANT SENSATION MEANS
THERE'S A FLAME HAZE NEARBY.
- HUH?  WHAT?
WHERE'S THE FLAME HAZE?
WHERE IS IT?  WHERE IS IT?
I WANT IT REAL BAD.
- AND IT'S NOT ALONE.
- HUH?
- IT'S GOING TO
DETECT US ANY SECOND NOW.
- IT'S NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
WE KNEW IT WAS ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME BEFORE WE EVENTUALLY
RAN ACROSS A FLAME HAZE.
- FINE THEN.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
- I WANTED MORE TIME TO PREPARE
SOME WELCOMING TRAPS,
BUT I THINK WE'LL BE FINE.
SO SHALL WE GET THIS UNDERWAY,
DEAR BROTHER?
BUT FIRST,
I THINK IT'S ONLY POLITE
THAT WE GO
AND PAY THEM A SOCIAL CALL.
'CAUSE AFTER ALL,
IT WON'T BE HARD TO FIND THEM.
- I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED
YESTERDAY.
- YEAH, REMEMBER WHEN ALASTOR
WAS ON THE PHONE?
HE SAID SOMETHING
HAPPENED YESTERDAY.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- HUH?
WHAT IS IT, SHANA?
- I PROMISED THAT I'M NEVER EVER
GOING TO DO IT WITH YOU.
- HEY, CARE FOR
A LITTLE COMPANY?
- HERE YOU GO, SAKAI.
I MADE YOU A LUNCH IF YOU WANT
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
- THAT'S FOR ME?
- YEAH, BECAUSE ALL YOU EVER EAT
AT LUNCH ARE RICE BALLS.
THAT'S WHY.
- SURE.
I APPRECIATE IT.
THANKS FOR LUNCH!
- ( sighs )
- OH, MAN, WHAT DO I START WITH?
IT ALL LOOKS GOOD.
I--
- YEP, YOU'RE SURE BUYING
A LOT OF STUFF.
- THAT'S AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED.
- Marco:
THIS ISN'T THE BEST TIME
TO RUN INTO SUCH HEAVY VISITORS.
- WHO ARE THOSE GUYS?
- BIG SISTER.
- IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE I LAST SAW YOU,
BEAUTIFUL SLAUGHTERER.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
YOU OUT OF SHAPE CASANOVA?
- YOU KNOW HER?
- INDEED, LET ME INTRODUCE
HER TO YOU, TIRIEL.
THE FLAME HAZE MARGERY DAW,
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
AS FAR AS KILLERS GO,
I'D SAY SHE'S PROBABLY THE BEST.
- WELL, THE CLAWS AND FANGS
OF VIOLATION.
- BUT I DON'T CARE WHO THEY ARE.
THEY DON'T HAVE
WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
- OH, I THOUGHT MAYBE
WE'D GOTTEN LUCKY,
BUT I GUESS THIS IS JUST
A RANDOM ENCOUNTER.
- SO LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- IF YOU INSIST, DEAR BROTHER.
- THOSE THREE ARE DENIZENS.
- SHOULD WE REALLY BE
LETTING THEM GO?
- WE DIDN'T LET THEM GO.
THEY LET US GO.
- SHUT UP, STUPID MARCO.
- SO WHAT DID YOU TALK
TO MY MOTHER ABOUT?
- NOTHING THAT YOU NEED
TO BE CONCERNED WITH.
YOU NEED TO FOCUS
ON YOUR TRAINING MORE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO EMBARRASS
YOUR MOTHER, NOW DO YOU?
- NO.
- YU-CHAN, SHANA-CHAN, COME IN,
DINNER'S READY.
- OKAY.
- YEAH, OKAY, MOM.
- Both: HUH?
- WHOA.
- I'LL NEVER DO IT WITH YOU.
- HMM?
- HMM, I WONDER
WHERE IT COULD BE,
THE NIETONO NO SHANA.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE GIRL WHO HAS
FEELINGS FOR YUJI DECLARES WAR.
A CHALLENGE THAT SHANA ACCEPTS.
THAT'S WHEN TIRIEL
MAKES HER MOVE,
AND ENGULFED IN LOVE FOR OTHERS,
SPRINGS HER TRAP.
NEXT EPISODE...