- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
( Mr. Kondo whistles )
- RIGHT, THE LAST
15 MINUTES WILL BE FREE TIME
- YAY.
- CANNONBALL.
- Mr. Kondo: HEY, CAN IT.
THAT WAS A DANGEROUS STUNT.
- Male student: ALL RIGHT.
- YOU LOOK A LITTLE LOST
WITHOUT YOUR BUDDY HERE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU GUYS FIGHT?
- NO, THAT ISN'T IT.
- AWW.
- SO I GUESS SATO
REALLY IS SICK TODAY.
- YEAH, HE IS.
BUT HEY, OGA-CHAN,
ARE YOU WORRIED
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T SHOW UP TODAY?
- HUH? IDIOT.
- ( sighs )
- DO YOU HAVE
FEELINGS FOR YOSHIDA?
- Do I?
- I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
I TELL HIM MY FEELINGS.
- NO, YUJI'S MINE.
- ( gasps )
- I'M GOING TO TELL HIM.
TELL HIM PROPERLY.
- HUH?
- I SAID, DO YOU
THINK THAT'S RIGHT?
IF YOU KEEP PLAYING
GAMES LIKE THIS,
YOU'RE GONNA END UP
HURTING SOMEONE.
- HMM.
- ( sighs )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT. I CAN SAY IT.
AS LONG AS I GET
THE OPPORTUNITY.
- I WON'T LOSE.
I'LL NEVER LOSE TO HER.
- Sydonay: THE PALACE OF THE
STARS IS PRACTICALLY EMPTY.
WHAT ARE YOU UPTO?
- WE'RE PLANNING ON USING
THE PALACE AS A VESSEL,
FOR THE TREASURE OF TREASURES,
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
AND FOR HECATE'S SAKE.
- Sydonay: ARE YOU
OKAY WITH THAT, HECATE?
- IF BEL PEOL WISHES,
THEN SO BE IT.
- AH, SHE'S WITHDRAWN AGAIN.
- MYSTERIOUS, YES.
BUT SHE THINKS ANSWERS WILL
COME TO HER WHEN SHE DOES IT.
- MY HECATE IS ALL ABOUT PURITY.
I JUST LOVE THAT ABOUT HER.
- ( chuckles )
- THIS LATEST PLAN, IT ISN'T
GOING TO HARM HER, IS IT?
- AH, NO. IN FACT,
IT SHOULD MAKE HER AN
EXISTENCE FOR ALL ETERNITY
EVEN AS WE SPEAK, SOMEONE
PERFECT FOR THE JOB
IS SETTING IT ALL UP,
ALTHOUGH I STILL HAVE SOME
UNANSWERED QUESTIONS ABOUT HIM.
- ( birds chirping )
- SO WHY AM I TRAINING ALONE?
WHAT'S SHANA DOING ANYWAY?
- Alastor: SHE DID NOT
SEE FIT TO TELL ME.
- YEAH BUT THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME THIS HAS EVER HAPPENED,
AS FAR AS I CAN REMEMBER.
DO YOU THINK SOMETHING
IMPORTANT HAS COME UP?
- Alastor: STOP TALKING
UNNECESSARILY.
PICK UP YOUR PACE.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- THERE, YOU'RE ALL SET.
BUT SERIOUSLY, YOU'VE NEVER
DONE ANY COOKING BEFORE?
- NONE. WIRHELMINA TOLD ME THAT
KIND OF TRAINING WASN'T NEEDED.
- MISS WIRHELMINA IS THE PERSON
WHO USED TO LIVE WITH
MR. ALASTOR, RIGHT?
- MMM.
- PREPARING A BOX LUNCH
MIGHT BE DIFFICULT
IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANY
EXPERIENCE AT ALL.
- HUH?
- DOES IT HAVE TO
BE A BOX LUNCH?
- MMM.
- DID YU-CHAN ASK
YOU TO MAKE HIM THIS?
- UH...
IT'S JUST, WELL...
I DIDN'T FEEL GOOD
WATCHING YUJI EAT THE BOX LUNCH
KAZUMI YOSHIDA MADE FOR HIM.
- KAZUMI YOSHIDA?
- SHE CAN COOK.
- WELL, LET'S START
WITH SOMETHING SIMPLE,
LIKE YOUR BASIC OMELETTE.
- SURE.
- ( panting )
- DON'T STOP, KEEP RUNNING.
- JUST HANG ON A SECOND.
LEMME CATCH MY BREATH, OKAY?
- YOU DISAPPOINT ME.
ALL RIGHT, JUST FOR A MOMENT.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- A SINGLE YES WILL DO.
- RIGHT, THE MISAGO FESTIVAL.
IT'S TOMORROW.
- WHAT ARE YOU REFERRING TO?
- UH, LOOK. IT'S AN ANNUAL
FESTIVAL. IT'S A PRETTY BIG ONE.
I USED TO GO TO IT ALL THE
TIME WITH MY MOM AND DAD.
- CANDY APPLES, MY FAVORITE.
- HMM?
- A SNACK. THEY SELL THEM
IN THE NIGHT STALLS.
I KNOW, I SHOULD COME
WITH SHANA TOMORROW.
- HMM, BUT I GUESS SHE'S NOT TOO
INTERESTED IN FESTIVALS.
- OF COURSE SHE ISN'T.
RESUME YOUR TRAINING.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- A SINGLE YES WILL DO.
- ( barking )
- OH, IT'S OKAY.
DON'T BE SCARED.
IT'S JUST A DECORATION
FOR THE FESTIVAL.
THE MISAGO FESTIVAL. IT'S THAT
TIME OF YEAR ALL READY.
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps )
- I KNOW, I'LL ASK SAKAI
TO THE FESTIVAL,
AND THAT'S WHERE
I'LL TELL HIM HOW I FEEL.
LET'S GO HOME EKATERINA. I'VE
GOTTA GET READY FOR SCHOOL.
- I THINK IT'S MY FAULT
FOR NOT WATCHING YOU MAKE IT.
- IT IS YOUR
FIRST TIME, AFTER ALL.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
IT'S BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
TRAINED ENOUGH.
- CALLING THIS "TRAINING" SEEMS
LIKE A BIT OF AN EXAGGERATION.
THE IMPORTANT
THING ABOUT COOKING
IS THAT YOU DO IT OUT OF LOVE.
- HUH? OUT OF LOVE?
- GEE, WHAT DO I START WITH?
IT ALL LOOKS SO GOOD.
- HMM.
- SHANA-CHAN,
WE'LL TAKE OUR TIME
AND LEARN THE BASICS PROPERLY.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT? THE MISAGO
FESTIVAL IS TOMORROW.
YOU SHOULD GO TO IT
WITH YU-CHAN.
- FESTIVAL? ONE OF
THOSE NOISY CELEBRATIONS?
- THEY'RE A LOT OF FUN. LISTEN,
COME HERE RIGHT AFTER SCHOOL.
- I'LL GET YOU A YUKATA.
- HMM.
- BUT DON'T TELL HIM
YOU'RE WEARING ONE.
YU-CHAN WILL BE DAZZLED
WHEN HE SEES HOW PRETTY
YOU LOOK IN YOUR YUKATA.
- YOU THINK SO?
- ( door opens )
- Yuji: I'M HOME.
- ( gasps )
- ( whirring )
- ( sniffs ) THAT'S WEIRD,
I SMELL SOMETHING BURNT.
- REALLY?
- YUJI, DID YOU FINISH
YOUR TRAINING?
- I SURE DID. SO, WHY DIDN'T
YOU COME OUT TODAY, SHANA?
- NO REASON.
- HMM.
- UM, YOU KNOW WHAT?
GO AHEAD, SHANA.
I HAVE TO GO AND BUY SOMETHING.
YOSHIDA'S REALLY NICE,
BUT I SHOULDN'T BE EATING
HER BOX LUNCHES.
- Clerk: THANK YOU, COME AGAIN.
- YOSHIDA. ER...
- JUST SAY IT. IF I DON'T FIND
THE COURAGE TO SAY IT NOW,
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO.
AND I'LL REGRET IT FOREVER.
- I WAS JUST UH...
- SAKAI.
- YES?
- TOMORROW, IT'S
THE MISAGO FESTIVAL.
DO YOU WANNA GO TO IT WITH ME?
- YOSHIDA...
- Boy: SO, YOU GOIN' TO
THE FESTIVAL TOMORROW?
SUPPOSED TO BE PRETTY COOL
THIS YEAR.
THEY'VE EVEN GOT A
BLIMP AND STUFF.
- YEAH, BUT IT WON'T
BE MUCH FUN JUST US TWO.
HEY, LET'S ASK SOME GIRLS TO GO.
- ( gasps )
- HEY, GOOD MORNING, IKE.
- HI.
- I WANT TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THE OTHER DAY.
I KNOW YOU SAID THOSE THINGS
BECAUSE YOU WANTED TO HELP ME.
- YOU KNOW, I SHOULD LEARN
TO KEEP MY MOUTH SHUT.
- MMM-MMM.
- I DECIDED TO DO WHAT I COULD
TO CHANGE THINGS ON MY OWN.
- HMM?
- IN FACT, YOSHIDA
WENT AND INVITED ME
TO THE MISAGO FESTIVAL TOMORROW.
- SO, YOU GOING?
- UH, YEAH.
- I SEE.
- BUT I DO UNDERSTAND WHAT
YOU SAID TO ME BEFORE, IKE.
- I THINK I'D BE ANGRIER
IF YOU TURNED HER DOWN
JUST BECAUSE YOU THOUGHT
I SHOULD HAVE A CHANCE WITH HER.
THE TRUTH IS, I'M STILL NOT SURE
WHETHER I HAVE FEELINGS FOR HER.
WHEN I KNOW FOR SURE,
THEN I'LL FIGHT FOR HER.
- HMM, RIGHT.
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
IT'LL BE MORE FUN AS A GROUP.
- OH, FOR SURE.
TANAKA, YOU WANT ME
TO COUNT YOU IN?
IT'S THE MISAGO FESTIVAL TOUR.
- UH, SORRY, NO.
I'VE KINDA GOT OTHER PLANS.
- OH, THAT'S OKAY. I WAS ONLY
JOKING. I DIDN'T REALLY MEAN IT.
- UNTIL NOW, FESTIVALS
NEVER MEANT ANYTHING TO ME.
- YU-CHAN WILL BE DAZZLED
WHEN HE SEES HOW PRETTY
YOU LOOK IN YOUR YUKATA.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE
THIS COULD BE FUN.
- ( groaning )
- Marco: HI!.
HOW YA FEELIN' BOSS?
- I'M GONNA REST
IN HERE FOR A WHILE.
- WHAT HAPPENED? WERE YOU
KICKED OUT OF A BAR AGAIN?
- ( coughs )
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SLEEP IN THEM YOU KNOW?
GO AHEAD AND USE ONE
OF THE OTHER ROOMS,
THERE'S NOBODY HERE.
- Marco: IF WE GET TOO
ATTACHED TO THIS PLACE,
IT'LL MAKE THINGS MORE
DIFFICULT WHEN WE LEAVE.
- BESIDES, YOUR MAID KEEPS
THIS PLACE TOO CLEAN FOR ME.
- IF THERE'S ONE THING
MY PARENTS INSIST ON,
IT'S MAKING SURE
THE HOUSE IS CLEAN.
- Marco: BUT THANKS TO THEM,
WE'VE GOT A PLACE WE CAN
ALWAYS STAY AT.
( laughs ) YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW WE APPRECIATE THAT.
- YEAH, I GUESS. THAT'S
A LOAD OFF MY MIND.
- HUH?
YOU'RE STILL A CHILD.
YOU JUST WANT SOMEONE
TO TAKE CARE OF YOU, RIGHT?
- ( laughs )
- WHAT WERE YOU EXPECTING?
- Marco: LEAVE HIM ALONE,
YOU'LL GIVE HIM A FEVER.
- OH COME ON, LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S ALL READY GETTING BETTER.
WELL, I'M GONNA GO TAKE A NAP.
- ( sighs )
CATCH YOU LATER.
- I ACTUALLY INVITED HIM.
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO
TELL HIM TOMORROW.
- HMM.
- Clerk: THANKS FOR COMING.
- ( chuckles )
- HUH?
- Khamsin: SO, TELL ME.
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
- WHAT?
- I PICKED UP A STRONG SCENT,
INDICATING THAT...
- Behemoth: HMM, PERHAPS
IT'S COMING FROM SOMEONE
WHO'S CLOSE TO THE GIRL,
SOMEONE WHO'S TRYING
TO HIDE HIM OR HERSELF.
- YEAH, I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- OH, I GUESS IT'S TIME FOR
INTRODUCTIONS.
I AM MOBILIZER OF
CEREMONIAL EQUIPMENT, KHAMSIN.
- AND THIS IS...
- I AM BEHEMOTH, THE
STEADFAST SHARP PEAK.
- WE ARE HERE TO ASK YOU
FOR YOUR COOPERATION.
WE THINK YOU'D BE PERFECT
FOR AN IMPORTANT JOB WE HAVE.
THERE'S NO DANGER.
WE ARE HERE TO FIX THE
DISTORTION WITHIN YOUR CITY.
NO, PLEASE DON'T BE FRIGHTENED.
LOOK THROUGH
THIS AND YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
- SEE HOW THE WORLD REALLY IS.
- THIS WORLD?
- HERE.
LOOK.
- ( gasps )
- ( wind howling )
- MARCOSIAS.
- Marco: YEAH, THEY'RE
HERE ALL RIGHT.
ALTHOUGH THEY DON'T SEEM TO BE
DOING ANYTHING. JUST OBSERVING.
- YOU' RE RIGHT. HMM.
- Tanaka: YOU MEAN
WITH BIG SISTER?
- Sato: IF MARGERY AND MARCO
DECIDE TO LEAVE THE CITY,
THEN I'M GONNA JOIN 'EM.
- HMM. THEN, I'LL GO TOO.
WE SHOULD START TRAINING FOR IT.
- TORCHES, THEY
REPLACE DEAD PEOPLE
WHO WERE EATEN BY MONSTERS...
IN THIS CITY?
- ( child laughing )
- ( laughing )
- WHAT ABOUT MY FAMILY?
WHAT'LL I DO IF THEY'RE...
IS MY FAMILY OKAY?
- PLEASE REST ASSURED.
YOUR FAMILY IS QUITE UNHARMED.
IT'S ONE OF THE CONDITIONS TO
HAVING YOU COOPERATE WITH US.
- THEY'RE SAFE?
- MY FATHER, MY MOTHER
AND MY LITTLE BROTHER, KEN?
- ( sighs in relief )
- ( gasps )
- HANG ON, WHAT ABOUT...
WHAT ABOUT SAKAI?
- TONIGHT WE'LL WORK ON
CONTROLLING POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- UH-HUH.
HEY SHANA, SINCE
TOMORROW'S SATURDAY,
OUR TRAINING'S IN THE
AFTERNOON, RIGHT?
- TOMORROW EVENING'S OKAY.
- UH, REALLY?
- I SAID SO, DIDN'T I?
- HMM.
- LET'S GET STARTED.
THAT'LL WORK. I CAN TRAIN WHEN
I GET BACK FROM THE FESTIVAL.
- YUJI, FOCUS.
- UH...
- I WANT YOU TO TRY
TO CONTROL THE AMOUNT
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE
YOU SEND TO ME.
- HUH? HMM.
- THIS TIME, GATHER AND RELEASE
IT IN A KIND OF EXPLOSION,
BUT MAKE SURE TO KEEP ENOUGH
FOR YOUR OWN EXISTENCE.
YUJI.
ALL YOU DID WAS INCREASE
THE AMOUNT YOU SENT TO ME.
YOU HAVE TO CAUSE
A BRIEF EXPLOSION.
YOU DON'T HAVE A LOT OF POWER OF
EXISTENCE TO PLAY AROUND WITH,
BUT RELEASE IT ALL AT ONCE
AND IT CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
- I'M HAVING TROUBLE JUDGING
HOW MUCH TO LEAVE BEHIND.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT A SAFE AMOUNT
IS FOR MY OWN EXISTENCE.
- Alastor: COME MIDNIGHT, THE
MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
WITHIN YOU WILL FULLY RECHARGE
YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
SO DON'T BE AFRAID TO USE IT UP.
- I KNOW, BUT...
- EVERY SINGLE NIGHT
YOU'RE OUT HERE PRACTICING.
- Marco: SORRY TO BOTHER YOU
ON SUCH A ROMANTIC EVENING.
- Yuji: HUH, GOOD EVENING.
- Shana: IS THIS ABOUT THAT
STRANGER I SENSED?
- YES. QUITE A SIGNIFICANT ONE.
- Marco: SEEMS TO BE A
FLAME HAZE.
IT'S REALLY STARTING
TO PISS ME OFF.
- HUH? IS THIS TRUE?
YOU NEVER TOLD ME ABOUT...
- I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
BECAUSE I SENSED THE VISITOR
WASN'T HERE TO FIGHT.
- WELL, IT IS POSSIBLE
WE HAVE A FLAME HAZE
WHO JUST HAPPENS TO BE
PASSING THROUGH,
EXCEPT FOR THE FACT WE'VE
GOT THIS CRAZY ITEM HERE.
- HUH.
- SO WE SHOULD BE VERY CAUTIOUS.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE HOW
HAPPY THAT BASTARD WAS
WHEN HE FOUND IT.
- ARE YOU CARRYING...
THAT'S WHY. I UNDERSTAND.
- I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU'VE HEARD THE LATEST,
BUT APPARENTLY SYDONAY IS ONCE
AGAIN A MEMBER
OF THE BALL MASQUE.
- ( gasps )
- Alastor: IS THIS CONFIRMED?
- THE BALL WHAT?
- THE BALL MASQUE,
A DENIZEN GROUP.
- ITS CORE IS COMPRISED OF
THREE POWERFUL DENIZENS
KNOWN AS THE TRINITY.
HECATE, BEL PEOL AND THOUGH HE
WAS AWAY FOR SOME TIME, SYDONAY.
- Marco: IF THEY DECIDE
TO MAKE THEIR PRESENCE KNOWN,
IT COULD BE TROUBLE
FOR ALL OF US.
- IT MAY BE TIME TO PLAN
IN WHAT DIRECTION
WE WISH TO GO FROM
THIS POINT ON.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M SAYING, YUJI SAKAI?
- UH, DIRECTION?
- I'M TALKING ABOUT
LEAVING THE CITY.
- HMM?
- THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE THAT
BALL MASQUE WILL COME TO
THE CITY IN AN ATTEMPT
TO ACQUIRE YOU, YUJI.
- THEY'RE RIGHT. EVERYONE'S
IN DANGER IF I STAY HERE.
- Khamsin: YES, I APOLOGIZE
FOR EXPOSING YOU
TO THE WORLD'S
REALITIES SO SUDDENLY.
HOWEVER, IF YOU'RE GOING
TO COOPERATE WITH US,
I HAD TO MAKE SURE YOU
UNDERSTOOD THE TRUTH
AND IRREGULARITIES
OF THIS WORLD.
LIKE YOU SAW EARLIER, THERE ARE
MANY TORCHES IN THIS CITY.
IT'S BADLY WARPED.
RESTORING THE ORDER OF THINGS
AND REPAIRING SUCH WARPS
IS OUR JOB.
- Behemoth: HMM, IN FACT,
HE'S KNOWN AS A "TUNER."
- IN ORDER TO TUNE A LOCATION,
WE REQUIRE THE COOPERATION
OF A HUMAN BEING WHO
WAS BORN AND RAISED...
- WHAT ABOUT SAKAI?
OH, SAKAI.
- WE WON'T LEAVE YET.
- RECKLESS MOVES ARE DANGEROUS.
- LEAVE THIS CITY?
TOGETHER. WITH SHANA.
- ( Professor laughs )
EVERYTHING SEEMS TO BE FALLING
INTO PLACE, AS EXPECTED.
- OH THAT VOICE. IT IS HIM.
- THE BALL MASQUE, I'M
SENSING STRANGE MOVEMENTS
AT THE PALACE OF THE STARS.
- Tiamat: THE
MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- AS SOON AS WE'RE DONE HERE,
WE'LL LOOK INTO IT.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE PROFESSOR IS GOING
TO CONDUCT AN EXPERIMENT
AT THE MISAGO FESTIVAL.
IN THE CONFUSION,
THE GIRLS' HEARTS REFLECT
THEIR PERSONAL DELUSIONS.
SHANA'S FACE SHOWS AN EMOTION
SHE'S NEVER KNOWN BEFORE.
NEXT EPISODE,
"A SHATTERED WISH."