- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Wirhelmina:
ONCE WE STORM IN THERE,
THERE WILL INDEED BE
NO TURNING BACK.
- I KNOW.
- AND OUR OBJECTIVE?
- Shana: THE ONLY
THING I'M CERTAIN OF
IS THAT I HAVE TO GO IN THERE.
- Wirhelmina: I UNDERSTAND.
IF WE GO, I'M SURE THE ANSWER
WILL BECOME CLEAR,
- BECAUSE YOU ARE A FLAME HAZE.
- YEAH.
- Tiamat: ENTER.
- SHANA.
SHE PROTECTED ME, EVEN THOUGH
I'M NOTHING BUT A MYSTES.
WHY?
- Shana: YUJI, I CAN FEEL YOU.
- THEY HAVE NOT SET UP
A PROTECTIVE SEAL.
- Alastor: YES,
BUT NOT SURPRISING,
CONSIDERING THEY KNEW WE
WERE GOING TO BE COMING.
- Tiamat: STAY FOCUSED.
- RIGHT.
- FLAME HAZES.
- HUH! SHANA.
- Wirhelmina: INDEED, I EXPECTED
TO SEE MORE DENIZENS
ROAMING THE PALACE OF THE STARS.
- IT'S TOO QUIET
AND THERE AREN'T ANY RINNE.
- I SENSE SOMETHING OVER THERE.
A VAST AMOUNT OF POWER OF
EXISTENCE IS POURING FORTH.
- THAT'S WHERE YUJI IS.
- Alastor: HMM.
- Wirhelmina: THEY'RE NOT EVEN
TRYING TO HIDE THE WHEREABOUTS
OF THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- Tiamat: A TRAP.
- Alastor: BUT, WE DON'T HAVE
THE LUXURY OF WORKING OUT
A PERFECT PLAN TO COUNTER
EVERY SITUATION.
- THEN YOUR NAME IS SHANA.
- LET'S GO.
- INDEED, THE MISSION
WILL BE A SUCCESS
IF EVEN ONE OF US GETS THROUGH
TO THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- GO FORWARD AND
HOLD NOTHING BACK.
- MMM.
- WHAT? WHAT IS YOUR ANSWER?
- Tiamat: TIME IS RUNNING OUT.
- Tanaka: SHE'S GOING UP
AGAINST THAT HUGE THING?
IS HIRAI GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
- Sato: WAIT, LOOK THERE.
THAT CASTLE HAS UNRESTRICTED
SYSTEM THINGS MOVING ALL OVER IT
- Professor: LOOK, THEY'RE HERE,
THE UNENLIGHTENED BRIGANDS
WHO WOULD OBSTRUCT
MY EXPERIMENT.
- DOMINO.
- I'M HERE. ALL THE
PREPARATIONS ARE COMPLETE.
- ( laughs ) WE'LL EXPERIMENT ON
THE EXPERIMENT OBSTRUCTORS.
THEY'LL PLAY A KEY ROLE
FOR THE THEME
OF MY WHOLE SACRED CHAPEL IS,
ECOLOGIZING AND RECYCLYZING.
- SOMETHING'S HERE.
- A DENIZEN.
- NO.
- ( creaking )
- Robots: LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT,
RIGHT, LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT...
- ( chanting )
- Domino: HALT.
- THESE GUYS.
- INDEED THESE ARE RINNE.
- Tiamat: AUTOMATONS.
- Alastor: THE SEEKER'S DOING.
- CHARGE.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE.
MY POWER OF EXISTENCE
HAS BEEN DRAINED.
- Wirhelmina: THIS MACHINE...
- Professor: IT'S A SUCCESS.
OH, THE UNRESTRICTED METHOD
DRAINS EXISTENCE
FROM TRESPASSERS
IN ORDER TO POWER MY RINNE.
IT'S FUNCTIONING EXCELLENTLY.
- Domino: YES, SIR, PROFESSOR.
WE'LL CONTINUE THE ATTACK.
- ( grunts )
- ( sighs )
- Alastor: HMM. CURSED SEEKER.
HOW OBSTRUCTIVE.
THAT'S WHY IT WAS SO EASY
TO GAIN ENTRANCE.
- HOW COME THEY'RE STILL MOVING?
- HE'S LIKELY EQUIPPED THEM
WITH SOME SPECIAL DEVICE
THAT EMPOWERS THEM.
- Wirhelmina: INDEED,
HERE THEY COME.
- ( grunting )
- THE NIETONO NO
SHANA IS HEAVY.
- Alastor: THE ONLY THINGS YOU
CAN COUNT ON ARE
THE PHYSICAL TECHNIQUES
YOU'VE LEARNED.
- REMEMBER THE LESSONS FROM
THE PALACE OF HEAVEN'S ROAD.
- RIGHT.
- ( grunts )
- WE'VE COME TOO FAR
TO TURN BACK. OUR ONLY...
CHANCE IS TO FIND
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- ( grunts )
INDEED HOW IRONIC, THERE'S
AN ENDLESS SUPPLY
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE OUTSIDE.
- SHANA. SHE'S FIGHTING.
- Hecate: FIGHTING.
- Yuji: POWER OF EXISTENCE
IS FLOWING INTO THE CITY,
BECAUSE OF
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
IT'S TRUE. IF I WANT TO
PROTECT THE CITY,
THEN MAYBE THIS IS FOR THE BEST.
- FOR THE BEST.
- Yuji: WHY?
- I'M NOTHING BUT A MYSTES.
- Yuji: HUH? STOP IT. WHY DO
YOU HAVE TO LOOK INSIDE ME?
- YOU'RE WRONG. YOU ARE
THE ONE WHO IS ENTERING ME.
YOUR THOUGHTS ARE FULFILLING ME.
I HAVE PRAYED FOR THIS MOMENT,
SEARCHED FOR AN ANSWER,
AND NOW IT IS HERE.
THAT'S WHY I WANT
MORE OF WHO YOU ARE.
- YOU'RE TAKING MY...
- YUJI.
- Bel Peol: WELL, I WONDER
HOW LONG THEY'RE GONNA LAST.
CARE TO MAKE A LITTLE WAGER.
- HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN, BEL PEOL,
WE'RE FIGHTING THE
FLAME OF HEAVEN
AND THE TIARA OF DREAMS
AND ILLUSIONS.
- BUT THE FLAME HAZES
THEY'RE USING HAVE BEEN
DENIED ACCESS TO
POWER OF EXISTENCE,
MAKING THEM NO DIFFERENT
THAN YOUR AVERAGE HUMAN.
BESIDES, WE'VE ALREADY
COMPLETED THE SACRED CHAPEL.
WE'LL BE COLLECTING POWER
OF EXISTENCE FOREVER NOW.
- ( both panting )
- READY, READY GO AND AIM.
- ( grunts )
- Tanaka: SO, SHE'S FIGHTING
IN THERE, RIGHT NOW?
- Sato: PROBABLY.
COME ON, HIRAI.
- WHAT THE...
- WARNING, THE
POWER OF EXISTENCE
HAS REACHED SATURATION POINT.
- ( screams )
- INDEED, THEY ARE ENDLESS.
- WAS THAT A PART
OF HIS CALCULATIONS?
- WHO KNOWS?
I GET THE FEELING WE'RE
IN UNKNOWN TERRITORY HERE.
- Professor: HOW EXCITING. WE'VE
NEVER SEEN THE LIKE BEFORE,
A WORLD FILLED TO THE BRIM
WITH POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- ( laughs )
- UH, PROFESSOR,
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN NEXT?
- I DON'T KNOW. THAT'S WHY
WE DO THESE EXPERIMENTS
IN ORDER TO FIND OUT
THE REAL TRUTH, THE REAL LAWS,
AND THE REAL STATE OF THE WORLD.
- SAKAI, YUKARI.
- ( screams )
- Sato: ALL RIGHT, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOIN' ON,
BUT I DO KNOW WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
- YEAH AND SO IS THE CITY.
- ( both sigh )
- Margery: HEY, GUYS.
ARE YOU THERE?
- HUH?
- KEISAKU, EITA.
YOU GUYS AREN'T DEAD, ARE YA?
- HELLO, IS ANYONE THERE?
KEISAKU, EITA.
- I... WE... YOU...
- ANSWER ME, RIGHT NOW.
- BIG SISTER.
- HMM.
- Tanaka: BIG SISTER.
- Marco: ( laughs ) GLAD TO HEAR
YOU TWO ARE STILL ALIVE.
- Tanaka: YOU DECIDED
TO COME BACK
- Margery: AH, IT'S
THE DUTY OF A FLAME HAZE.
- Marco: OH, AS IF. YOU WENT
ALL PALE AND THEN RUSHED, OW.
- ANYWAY, I NEED YOU TO GET
TO THE CRYSTAL ALTAR,
THERE'S SOMETHING I WANNA CHECK.
- Tanaka: ALL READY THERE.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU SHOULD KNOW.
- LISTEN, WE'VE BEEN WAITING
AT THE CRYSTAL ALTAR FOR YOU,
NOW HURRY UP AND TELL US
WHAT TO LOOK FOR.
- Marco: ( laughs )
THAT'S THE WAY TO TELL HER.
- HA, ALL RIGHT, I'LL PRETEND I
DIDN'T JUST HEAR YOU SNAP AT ME.
- TAKE A LOOK AT
THE PALACE OF STARS.
- Tanaka: PALACE OF STARS?
- Margery: THE HUGE CASTLE
FLOATING IN THE SKY...
I'M PRETTY SURE THE LITTLE BRAT
WENT IN THERE, BUT THERE'S THIS
STRANGE UNRESTRICTED
METHOD AROUND IT.
- Tanaka: UH, YEAH,
THAT'S RIGHT.
- Margery: TRACE IT BACK TO
FIND OUT WHAT PART OF THE
CASTLE IT'S COMING
FROM AND HURRY.
- RIGHT. WILL DO.
- Marco:
THEY'RE PRETTY RELIABLE,
A RESULT OF YOUR
INFLUENCE I'D SAY.
- GUESS SO.
-SATO, SHE CAME BACK.
BIG SISTER ACTUALLY CAME BACK.
- YEAH, SHE SURE DID.
SHE JUST COMES AND GOES.
RIGHT THERE.
- Margery: PLAY ONE
MORE PRETTY MELODY.
- Marco: HEY, PLAY ONE MORE
PRETTY MELODY.
- PLEASE, DEAR, WILL YOU
PLAY ONE FOR ME?
- Marco: HEY, PLAY ONE MORE
PRETTY MELODY.
- ( grunts )
- Both: GOODBYE AND GOODNIGHT.
- ( screams ) WHY HAS MY
MACHINE STOPPED FUNCTIONING?
- Domino: UH, THE DEVICE
THAT POWERS OUR
SPECIAL UNRESTRICTED METHOD...
IT APPEARS TO BE BROKEN.
- THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
- ( speaks incoherently )
- Sydonay: IT SEEMS THE CHANTER
OF ELEGIES HAS RETURNED.
- OH WELL, WHY DO FLAME HAZES
HAVE A TENDENCY TO SMASH ANY NEW
EXPERIMENTS THEY ENCOUNTER?
- IF SHE'S COME THIS FAR,
THEN PRETTY SOON,
SHE'S GONNA BE A
DISTRACTION TO HECATE.
I THINK I'LL GO AND GREET HER.
- THEN I GUESS I'LL
HAVE TO GO SAY HELLO
TO OUR FIRST TWO GUESTS.
- INDEED, IT APPEARS
WE HAVE BEEN SAVED
BY THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- Shana: YEAH.
SHE'S HERE.
- THIS ENERGY...
JUDGE OF PARADOXES.
- HELLO THERE, BEEN A WHILE
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
- I PREFER THAT YOU
NOT GET IN OUR WAY.
- Marco: CAN'T AGREE TO THAT,
NOT AFTER ALL THE WEIRD THINGS
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN DOING.
- Margery: TODAY ISN'T A DAY
FOR BACKING DOWN.
WE'RE SWIMMING
IN POWER RIGHT NOW.
WHY DON'T WE MAKE THIS
A FIGHT TO REMEMBER?
- ALL RIGHT THEN, LET'S
END THIS BEFORE WE GROW
TOO FOND OF EACH OTHER.
- ( both growling )
- YOU SHOULD GO ON. WE'LL BE OK
AS LONG AS ONE OF US MAKES IT.
- I HOPE YOU KNOW WHAT
YOUR ANSWER IS BY NOW.
- AND WILL YOU
INDEED DESTROY IT?
- I WON'T DO IT.
- THEN YOU'RE WILLING TO HAVE
THE WORLD THROWN OUT OF BALANCE?
- I WON'T LET IT.
WIRHELMINA, I AM THE FLAMING-
HAIRED BLAZING-EYED HUNTER,
BUT I AM ALSO SHANA.
MY MISSION IS CLEAR, BUT I WILL
NOT DESTROY THE MYSTES, YUJI.
THEY ARE THE SAME, AND
WITHOUT HIM, I AM NOT ME.
I AM NOT ONLY A FLAME HAZE.
I AM SHANA, WITH THE FLAMING
HAIR AND BLAZING EYES,
AND I FIGHT FOR MY BELIEFS.
THAT IS MY ANSWER.
- THEN GO ON AHEAD.
IF YOU'VE MADE YOUR DECISION,
I INDEED HAVE NOTHING
MORE TO SAY TO YOU.
- WIRHELMINA.
- I'VE FAITH IN YOU
WITHOUT RESERVATION OR DOUBT,
I DO INDEED BELIEVE IN YOU.
- THEN WE'RE OFF.
WE SHALL MEET AGAIN,
SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING,
TIARA OF DREAMS AND ILLUSIONS.
- OH, HOW SAD TO SEE YOU
RUNNING AWAY FROM ME.
- INDEED, I AM
TO BE YOUR OPPONENT.
- Tiamat: COMMENCE BATTLE.
- LOVELY. YOU AND I
ARE GONNA HAVE SOME FUN.
- ALASTOR, YOU ASKED ME
WHAT I WANTED TO DO WITH YUJI
OR MORE LIKE WHAT
I WANTED HIM TO DO.
- I STILL DON'T KNOW YET.
- I SEE.
- AND YET I LOVE YUJI.
- THAT'S ALL I DO KNOW.
- HMM.
- YES, THAT'S ENOUGH.
I CAN FIGHT WITH JUST THAT.
- Yuji: THEN YOUR NAME IS SHANA.
THAT'S WHAT I'LL CALL YOU.
STOP SAYING YOU'RE ONLY
A FLAME HAZE.
- Hecate: SHANA, FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED FLAME HAZE.
- Yuji: YES. I GAVE
HER THAT NAME.
SINCE THEN, THE BLAZING-EYED
HUNTER HAS BEEN CALLED SHANA.
- YUJI.
- NOW I SEE. SHE PROTECTED
ME, BECAUSE SHE'S SHANA.
- Hecate: BECAUSE SHE'S SHANA.
- RIGHT, SHE'S NOT JUST
A FLAME HAZE. BUT I WAS...
- I WAS THE ONE WHO
ONLY SAW HER AS A FLAME HAZE.
IT WAS ME.
- YUJI.
- SHANA.
- AN OBSTACLE.
- YUJI, I AM COMING FOR YOU.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: SHAKUGAN NO SHANA,
FINAL EPISODE,
"CRIMSON THOUGHTS."
AT THAT MOMENT, A SMILE FROM THE
GIRL STEPPING INTO THE FLAMES.