- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
( grunting )
- WHAT'S THIS?
- THAT'S AWESOME, TIRIEL!
WE CAUGHT HER!
- YES, OF COURSE WE DID,
DEAR BROTHER.
AFTER ALL, FLAME HAZES IN
GENERAL AREN'T VERY SMART.
SHE SAW THE ENORMOUS FLOWER
AND IMMEDIATELY JUMPED TO
THE WRONG CONCLUSION
THAT THE PLANT
WAS OUR WEAK SPOT.
THIS IS A RINNE, CALLED PINION.
DESTROY ITS FLOWERS,
AND NEW ONES GROW
ALMOST INSTANTANEOUSLY.
- ( grunts )
- I CAN'T WAIT, TIRIEL!
THAT'S THE NIETONO NO SHANA!
OH, CAN I HAVE IT NOW? PLEASE?
- OH, YES DEAR BROTHER.
YOU CAN HAVE IT.
- I THINK IT'S TIME YOU
HANDED OVER YOUR SWORD.
- NEVER!
- ( screams )
- THE NIETONO NO SHANA!
- HUH?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WANDERING AROUND OUT HERE?
- Yuji: IT'S YOU.
- INCREDIBLE. I DIDN'T BELIEVE
IT WHEN I SAW SOMEONE MOVING.
THEN I REALIZED IT HAD TO
BE YOU ROAMING THE STREETS.
- YES. SEE,
I'M TRYING TO...
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- BE QUIET.
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
- IT'S A TYPE OF RINNE.
I THINK WE SHOULD
GET OUTTA HERE.
- ( panting )
CAN YOU HEAR ME? IT'S EXACTLY
WHO I THOUGHT IT'S GOING TO BE.
- Tanaka: YOU MEAN IT
WAS THE OTHER
FLAME HAZE'S ATTENDANT
OUT THERE?
THAT'S THE ONE CALLED
A MYSTES, RIGHT?
- Margery: THAT'S RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW IF
HE FEELS OBLIGATED TO HER
OR IF HE'S IN LOVE
WITH THE LITTLE BRAT.
WHAT HE'S DOING IS RECKLESS.
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- Margery: YOU GUYS SEE
ANYTHING ELSE UNUSUAL?
- Yuji: UM, WHO ARE
YOU TALKING TO?
- Margery: I'M TALKING
TO MY HENCHMEN.
HEY, WAKE UP!
ANYTHING ELSE MOVING?
- Tanaka: BIG SISTER? DID YOU
JUST CALL US YOUR HENCHMEN?
- Margery: WHAT?
- Tanaka: I MEAN, THAT'S
WHAT IT SOUNDED LIKE.
WE JUST WANNA SAY WE'RE HONORED
THAT YOU SEE US THAT WAY.
- OH, WHAT A COUPLE OF...
COME ON! IS ANYTHING
MOVING OUT HERE?
- ( Marco laughs )
- Marco: I THINK YOU'RE
BLUSHING, MY NAIVE LITTLE...
- Yuji: THAT'S NOT HOW
ALASTOR'S TREATED.
SHE'S DIFFERENT.
- Tanaka: UM, THAT
BIG FLOWER FROM BEFORE
LOOKS LIKE ITS SET THINGS UP
SO ALL THE AREAS
ACT LIKE PIPELINES.
- Sato: NOTHING ELSE
HAS CHANGED.
THE UNRESTRICTED METHOD STILL
HAS EVERYTHING WRAPPED UP
AND THE TORCHES HAVEN'T MOVED.
- HMM... COME TO THINK OF
IT, I FORGOT TO ASK
WHAT YOU WERE DOING OUT
HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- WELL, IT'S NO MYSTERY. SHANA
SAID THERE MIGHT BE A DEVICE
GATHERING POWER OF EXISTENCE,
SO I WAS LOOKING FOR IT.
- Marco: HEY, HEY,
WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU SAYING YOU DETECTED
SOME KIND OF OBJECT
AND YOU WERE TRACKING IT
BEFORE THE FLOWER BLOOMED?
- UH, YES, SORT OF.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER NOW,
BECAUSE I'D NEVER BE ABLE
TO GET PAST THAT THING
TO DESTROY THE DEVICE.
- Margery: I GUESS THERE IS
SOMETHING SPECIAL ABOUT YOU.
YOU KEPT YOUR HEAD AND
FOUND OUT WHERE THE RINNE WAS
IN ALL THIS CONFUSION.
- OH, YEAH? YOU THINK SO?
- WITH YOUR HELP, WE MAY BE ABLE
TO MAKE THIS INTERESTING.
IT WOULD MEAN TEAMING UP WITH
THE LITTLE BRAT. YOU IN?
- I GOT IT!
MY NIETONO NO SHANA!
- THAT'S SIMPLY
WONDERFUL, DEAR BROTHER.
IT'S TIME, DEAR BROTHER.
- RIGHT, HERE'S YOUR REWARD.
- HEY SHANA,
IF I END UP HELPING YOU,
HOW 'BOUT YOU GIVE
ME A LITTLE REWARD?
- Chigusa: SHANA-CHAN, THIS IS
HOW I FEEL ABOUT A KISS,
IF IT'S ON THE LIPS,
THEN IT'S LIKE A PERSONAL OATH.
- Shana: NO, IT'S DIFFERENT
WITH THESE TWO.
- I HAVE AN IDEA, WHY DON'T YOU
TEST IT ON HER, DEAR BROTHER.
- TEST IT OUT?
AW, YEAH, FOR SURE!
- ( gasps )
THIS IS GREAT, TIRIEL!
THE BLADE DOESN'T EVEN
CHIP WHEN I CUT THE CHAIN!
- MY BROTHER LOVES TO
TEST HIS NEW TOYS
ON ANY UNLUCKY FLAME
HAZES WE RUN ACROSS.
CLOTHES COME FIRST,
THEN SKIN AND FLESH AND BONES,
THEN EACH INTERNAL ORGAN.
WELL, THIS ISN'T ANY FUN.
SHE'S FINISHED, BUT SHE HASN'T
MADE ANY DESPERATE THREATS
OR EVEN BROKEN
DOWN IN TEARS YET.
- YOU KISS,
BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME.
IT'S NOT AN OATH FOR YOU TWO.
- AN OATH?
YES, THAT'S ONE WAY TO PUT IT.
I GIVE MY BROTHER UNCONDITIONAL
JOY, WHICH IN TURN SATISFIES ME.
TOGETHER, WE SING THE PRAISES OF
THE EMOTION CALLED LOVE.
YOU ARE A TOOL OF DESTRUCTION,
THE PUPPET OF SOME LORD.
AND I PERSONALLY DON'T CARE
WHAT YOU THINK OF US.
- NO, YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
IT'S NOT LOVE. IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE JUST
HANGING ONTO EACH OTHER.
- Tiriel: PERHAPS
THE CONVERSATION
WAS A LITTLE TOO ADVANCED
FOR A MERE CHILD.
IT WAS POINTLESS TALKING TO
SOMEONE LIKE YOU ABOUT LOVE.
YOU'RE A TOOL FOR DESTRUCTION.
I WILL FULFILL ALL OF
MY BROTHER'S DESIRES.
I WILL PROTECT HIM!
I DO EVERYTHING FOR HIM!
- YUJI AND I AREN'T LIKE THEM.
IT'S DIFFERENT.
- ( explosion )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- MADNESS,
GET THEE TO A NUNNERY.
- Marco: OH, BOY, JUST BECAUSE
YOU CAN'T REMEMBER
ANY OF YOUR SONGS,
DO YOU HAVE TO USE
SOMETHING SO CRUDE?
- BUT WE GET
THE SAME EFFECT.
THAT'S NUMBER 5. ON TO THE NEXT.
- THE NEXT ONE IS
THAT MAN STANDING
IN FRONT OF THE GAS STATION.
- I HEAR YA. IT WON'T BE LONG.
THEY'RE GONNA SENSE THIS.
- SOMEHOW THEY'RE FINDING ALL OF
THE PINIONS AND DESTROYING THEM.
IT'S THAT FLAME HAZE.
HOW IS SHE DOING IT?
SYDONAY, ARE YOU THERE?
- Sydonay: YEAH.
- Tiriel: THAT OTHER FLAME HAZE
IS ON THE MOVE.
- WE SHOULD
LEAVE HER ALONE.
IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
MY ORDERS WERE TO JUST
PROTECT THE ORGEL.
- ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- Tiriel: THINGS HAVE CHANGED.
IF SHE KEEPS THIS UP, THE SPELL
OF THE CRADLE GARDEN
WILL BE BROKEN.
NOW HURRY!
- I SEE NO PROBLEM IN
LEAVING THINGS AS THEY ARE.
YOU GOT THE SWORD YOU
WERE AFTER, DIDN'T YOU?
- Tiriel: LISTEN,
WE CAN'T LET SOMEONE
GET AWAY WHO CAN SEE THROUGH
THE PINION'S CAMOUFLAGE.
- Sydonay: ALL RIGHT. IT IS
MY JOB TO PROTECT YOU
FROM THE FLAME HAZES.
- HMM...
OH, DEAR BROTHER, I'M AFRAID
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
LET'S BURN HER
WITH A SINGLE THRUST.
- THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
IT IS A FLAMING SWORD.
- BURNED ALIVE.
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO KNOW YOU'LL
DIE BY YOUR OWN SWORD?
- YUJI WILL TAKE CARE
OF THINGS. HE CAN DO IT.
- GOODBYE, TOOL FOR DESTRUCTION.
YOU'RE ALL ALONE,
AND YOU'LL LEAVE THIS WORLD
IN A BURST OF FIRE.
- I'M NOT ALONE!
I'M NOT A TOOL!
THERE ARE TWO OF US,
BUT WE CAN BE APART.
WE CAN FEEL EACH OTHER
AND GIVE EACH OTHER STRENGTH.
I AM A FLAME HAZE.
I HAVE MADE A VOW,
AND I AM DETERMINED TO KEEP
THE BALANCE OF THE WORLD.
THAT IS MY MISSION.
- STRIKE HER NOW!
- SWORD OF FIRE!
- IT'S DONE LIKE THIS!
- ( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- THAT'S BLOOD SUCKER!
- DEAR BROTHER!
- Shana: HERE, CATCH!
- ( gasps )
- Sydonay: I'M PLEASED THAT YOU
FOUND THE COURAGE
TO STEP FORWARD
AND MAKE YOUR PRESENCE KNOWN,
BEAUTIFUL SLAUGHTERER.
- HOW ABOUT YOU GIVE
THE NONSENSE A REST,
AND SHOW US WHAT YOU
REALLY LOOK LIKE.
- FAIR ENOUGH.
EXCHANGING PLEASANTRIES AS
BEASTS MIGHT BE WHAT I NEED.
- ( growling )
- Marco: THOUSAND CHANGES! YOU
COULDN'T PICK JUST ONE ANIMAL?
- Sydonay:
COME, TAKE A CLOSER LOOK,
FANGS AND CLAWS OF VIOLATION.
IT'LL BE THE LAST THING
YOU'LL EVER SEE!
- WHERE IS IT?
IT'S SOMEWHERE NEAR.
I THINK UP THERE.
- Sydonay: IT'S TOO BAD,
CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
YOU'VE BECOME SOFT.
HOW DISAPPOINTING.
- HE'S RIGHT,
I CAN'T FIGHT BACK.
AND I DON'T EVEN FEEL
THAT BAD ABOUT IT.
- Sydonay: LET US END THIS.
HOPE YOU AT LEAST HAVE FUN
IN HELL, MARGERY DAW.
- Shana: WHAT'S THIS?
SOMEHOW THEY'VE
HEALED THEIR INJURIES,
AND THEY'VE EVEN
PUT OUT THE FLAMES.
- GIVE IT.
MY NIETONO NO SHANA.
- YOU'D BETTER
HAND IT OVER.
- YOU'RE FADING.
- IT'S TRUE, YOU SEE, THERE WAS
ENOUGH POWER OF EXISTENCE
TO HEAL MY BROTHER'S INJURIES
AND STOP YOUR ATTACK,
BUT THAT USED UP THE LAST OF IT.
- THEREFORE...
- WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
- I TOLD YOU WHY.
I AM HERE TO FULFILL
THE DESIRES OF MY BROTHER
AND TO PROTECT HIM.
- BECAUSE YOU LOVE HIM?
- THAT'S RIGHT, I DO.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO TASTE THIS
UNBEARABLE FEELING AS WELL?
RIGHT NOW, THERE'S A YOUNG MAN
ON THAT BRIDGE WHO'S MOVING.
- ( grunting )
- I JUST CAN'T DO IT.
IT'S TOO FAR.
- ( gasps )
- Sydonay: YOU THERE,
WHY ARE YOU MOVING?
ARE YOU A MYSTES?
- HE REALLY DID A NUMBER ON US.
- Marco: YEAH,
BUT YOU DID A PRETTY GOOD JOB
IN THE MAGIC TRICKS DEPARTMENT.
YOU TOSSED OUT A DUMMY JUST
BEFORE THIS PLACE COLLAPSED
AND THEN STAYED CALM
SO WE WOULDN'T BE NOTICED.
HE'S UNDER THE ASSUMPTION
WE WERE KILLED.
- CONSIDERING I CAN'T
CHANT SONGS ANYMORE,
THAT WAS THE BEST I COULD DO.
IN ANY CASE, WE SHOULD FIND OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON OUTSIDE.
KEISAKU, EITA.
HEY, KEISAKU, EITA,
COME ON, ANSWER ME!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Marco: I LOST CONTACT
WITH THEM A WHILE AGO.
- WHAT?
- Marco: I DIDN'T HEAR
A SINGLE WORD FROM
ALL THE TIME YOU WERE
UNCONSCIOUS. NOT A SOUND.
- WAIT JUST A MINUTE HERE!
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU DON'T...
MARCOSIAS!
- Marco: BUT, IT'S WHAT
YOU WANTED, ISN'T IT?
OH, MY LAZY FOOL, MARGERY DAW.
STAYING INDOORS FOR DAYS ON END.
MAKING EXCUSES ABOUT HOW YOU'VE
BECOME NOTHING
BUT AN EMPTY SHELL.
AND NOW LOOK WHAT'S HAPPENED.
WHAT RIGHT DO YOU HAVE TO
COMPLAIN? AND WHO WOULD CARE?
- BUT I... BUT I...
HOW MANY HUNDREDS OF YEARS
HAVE I BEEN FIGHTING?
ALWAYS CHASING SILVER,
PURSUING HIM.
YOU COULD CUT ME A LITTLE SLACK.
- Marco: IF THAT WAS ALLOWED,
THEN WE'D ALL BE SITTING PRETTY,
BUT IT ISN'T. YOU'VE GOTTA
PULL YOUR OWN WEIGHT.
THAT'S THE WAY THE WORLD WORKS.
- Margery: ONCE MORE, I STAND ON
MY FEET. I RISE FROM THE DEPTHS,
AND I START AGAIN.
- ( Marco whooping )
- ( growling )
- YOU GUYS!
MARCO! WHAT IS THIS?
- ( laughing )
- Marco: TECHNICALLY
I WASN'T LYING.
I TOLD THEM YOU
WERE DOWN THERE,
BUT I NEVER
RECEIVED AN ANSWER.
- YOU... HOW DARE YOU?
- I'M SO GLAD YOU MADE IT!
- Marco: WATCH OUT, EITA.
IT'S DANGEROUS TO GET
TOO CLOSE TO HER.
YOUR BIG SISTER DOESN'T
LIKE TO LOSE,
AND SHE'S ANGRY RIGHT NOW.
THAT MEANS SHE'S SERIOUS.
- BUT SHE'S BEEN INJURED.
- Marco: DON'T WORRY,
SHE'S USED TO FAR WORSE.
NOW, HURRY BACK
TO THE CRYSTAL ALTAR.
- OKAY THEN,
WE'LL HEAD RIGHT OVER THERE.
- BLAST HIM! SHOW THAT
DENIZEN WHO'S BOSS, BIG SISTER!
- WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
I LOOK LIKE A COMPLETE IDIOT
BACK THERE, YOU KNOW.
- Marco: YOU WANNA QUIT?
- YOU'VE GOTTA BE
KIDDING. QUIT NOW?
I HAVE SOMETHING
I WANNA PROTECT.
- ( screaming )
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
HIDING INSIDE YOU,
BUT I'M TAKING IT.
- SHANA.
- ARE YOU CARRYING...
THAT'S WHY. I UNDERSTAND.
- WELL, IT'S MINE NOW.
- SMASH HIM!
- CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- NICE TIMING, EH, KID?
- Marco: TIME TO ROLL UP THE
SLEEVES, WE'RE HERE TO FIGHT!
- PENNIES, PENNIES, PENNIES IN
A SACK BRINGS A MILLION BACK.
WELL, WELL, WELL.
I GUESS I DON'T NEED TO BE
FULL OF HATE TO FIGHT.
- Marco: LOOKS THAT WAY!
- SHANA!
- YUJI!
- Yuji: THAT'S IT.
- Shana: NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
THAT'S THE TREASURE RUNNING
THEIR UNRESTRICTED METHOD.
- Tiriel: YES.
THE CRADLE GARDEN IS MAINTAINED
AND CONTROLLED BY THE ORGEL.
NO MATTER HOW COMPLICATED
THE UNRESTRICTED METHOD IS,
THE ORGEL WILL PLAY
THE SAME TUNE OVER AND OVER.
- HER BODY. IT'S FADING.
- MY NIETONO NO SHANA. GIVE IT!
- Margery: RING AROUND
THE ROSEY.
- Marco: A POCKET FULL
OF POSIES.
- DAMN IT, IF THIS KEEPS UP,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO HELP THEM.
ARE THE SIBLINGS
STILL IN THE GAME?
CRIMSON WINGS?
IT'S FLAMING-HAIR BLAZING-EYES.
- Margery: HEADS UP!
- THE ENGULFED IN LOVE SIBLINGS
ARE FINISHED. IT'S TIME I LEFT.
- THOUSAND CHANGES
IS RUNNING AWAY.
- ( gasps )
- MY PRECIOUS BROTHER!
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
I WILL MAKE HAPPEN.
- HUH?
NIETONO!
- SORRY.
- I SEE I'M NOT THE
ONLY ONE WHO'S FINISHED.
THOSE DEGENERATES
AND THEIR UNRESTRICTED METHOD.
I MADE A FEW CHANGES
HERE AND THERE.
IT'S CRAZY HOW MUCH POWER
OF EXISTENCE THEY'D GATHERED.
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO PUT THE CITY
BACK TOGETHER
WITH NO REAL PROBLEM.
- Shana: HURRY UP, THE SEAL'S
COMING DOWN SOON.
- Yuji: I KNOW.
WE NEED TO GET BACK.
SO WHERE WERE YOU, SHANA?
- WELL, I WAS...
SHUT UP! SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
NOWHERE.
- ALL RIGHT THEN. SEE YA.
- NO, YUJI, WAIT.
DURING THIS BATTLE,
YOU DID A GREAT JOB
TRACKING DOWN THE PINIONS
AND HELPING OUT THE
CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
THEREFORE, I WILL REWARD YOU.
- WHAT?
- DOES SHE MEAN REALLY?
IS... IS IT OKAY?
- HAVE SOME
MELON BREAD. ENJOY!
- HUH?
- YOU WERE SAYING? GO ON!
- ANYWAY, YOU CAN'T
GO AFTER YUJI.
- SURE I CAN. YOU ARE
BEING SO UNFAIR ABOUT THIS,
AND I'M GONNA TELL
SAKAI THAT I LOVE HIM.
AND WHEN I DO,
YOU'LL BE OUT OF THE PICTURE.
- IT IS NOT UNFAIR.
YOU CAN'T GO AFTER HIM,
'CAUSE YUJI IS MY...
YUJI IS MY WHAT?
BELIEVE ME, IT'S BETTER FOR
YUJI TO BE WITH ME THAN YOU.
- THAT IS NOT TRUE. SAKAI SHOULD
BE THE ONE TO DECIDE THAT.
- BUT YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT YUJI.
- I'LL GET TO KNOW HIM.
- YOU CAN'T!
- WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE I SAY SO.
- I SAID WHAT I HAD TO SAY.
- FORGET IT.
I WON'T LOSE TO YOU.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE FLAME-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED FLAME HAZE.
ONCE THERE WAS A FAMOUS LADY WHO
HAD A GREAT INFLUENCE ON HER.
A STORY FROM SHANA'S PAST
ABOUT WIRHELMINA CARMEL.
NEXT EPISODE, "A GREAT PERSON."