- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
Yoshida: THE WAY THE
WORLD REALLY IS.
- Khmasin: I WILL LEND YOU
THAT MONOCLE.
PLEASE CONFIRM FOR YOURSELF
WHETHER OR NOT
THE PERSON YOU KNOW AS YUJI
SAKAI IS INDEED A TORCH.
I'M GOING TO NEED
YOUR COOPERATION,
AND THAT WOULD BE DIFFICULT
IN YOUR PRESENT STATE.
- Behemoth: YOUNG LADY,
IT IS CRUCIAL TO HAVE SOMEONE
LIKE YOU WHO IS BORN
AND RAISED IN THE CITY,
SOMEONE WHO KNOWS IT
AND HOLDS IT IN HER HEART.
- Yoshida: IF SAKAI IS A TORCH,
THEN ONE DAY...
HE'S JUST FINE.
I'M SURE HE'S NOT A TORCH.
AND AT THE FESTIVAL TOMORROW,
I'M GONNA TELL HIM
THAT I LOVE HIM.
- Shana: THERE'S A PRETTY GOOD
CHANCE THE BALL MASQUE
IS GOING TO COME TO THIS
CITY LOOKING FOR YOU, YUJI.
THIS PLACE IS
ALREADY UNBALANCED,
SO WE COULD HAVE A REAL
PROBLEM ON OUR HANDS.
- Yuji: I CAN'T STAY IN THIS
CITY FOR MUCH LONGER,
REGARDLESS OF WHAT
THE BALL MASQUE DOES.
I'M NO LONGER HUMAN,
AND ONE OF THESE DAYS,
I'M GONNA HAVE TO SAY GOODBYE
TO MOM AND EVERYONE ANYWAY.
BUT I WANNA STAY JUST
A LITTLE LONGER,
HANG ON A LITTLE WHILE.
- Shana: I'M GONNA WEAR A YUKATA
TOMORROW AND SURPRISE YUJI.
AND THEN WE'LL GO TO
THE FESTIVAL TOGETHER.
- ( giggles )
JUST LIKE THE DAY WE FINALLY
LEAVE THIS CITY,
WE'LL BE TOGETHER.
- Margery: WHAT? YOU BOTH
WANNA COME WITH ME
WHEN I DECIDE TO
LEAVE THIS PLACE?
- Marco: ( chuckles )
THESE GUYS MUST BE TOTALLY
INFATUATED WITH YOU.
OW!
- Margery: DO YOU TWO
REALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE TALKIN' ABOUT HERE?
- Sato: OF COURSE WE DO.
- I'M NOT SO SURE ABOUT THAT.
- ( grunting )
- WHAT YOU GUYS ARE TRYING
TO ACHIEVE IS RIGHT HERE.
- I GET IT.
ONCE WE GET GOOD ENOUGH WITH IT,
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE US WITH YOU.
AM I RIGHT?
- YOU'LL UNDERSTAND WHEN
YOU GIVE IT A TRY.
- ALRIGHT!
- ( grunting )
- TANAKA!
- YOU THINK MAYBE THIS IS SOME
KINDA SUBTLE HINT
THAT SHE DOESN'T WANT
US TO COME ALONG?
- Marco: THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU.
- REALLY?
- USUALLY YOU JUST PUNCH
THEM IN THE FACE.
( laughs ) IT'S SO UNEXPECTED.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED TO FIND
IT RAINING BOOZE TOMORROW.
- ( Marco screams)
- Girl: HEY, YOU WEARING YOUR
YUKATA TO THE FESTIVAL?
- OH YEAH, ESPECIALLY
SINCE I JUST BOUGHT A NEW ONE.
- Alastor: I'M TALKING ABOUT
LEAVING THE CITY.
- Yoshida: I'M STILL AFRAID.
I'M STILL TOO AFRAID.
- YOSHIDA!
HEY IF IT'S OKAY, I'LL MEET YOU
ON THE BRIDGE AT 5 O'CLOCK.
- YEAH, SURE, THAT'S JUST FINE.
- Behemoth: HMM, I WONDER
HOW THAT GIRL IS DOING.
I CAN ONLY HOPE THIS YUJI SAKAI
OF HERS IS NOT A TORCH.
- Khamsin: AND I HOPE SHE CALMS
DOWN ENOUGH TO BE OF USE TO US.
IT'S GONNA TAKE A LOT OF
WORK TO TUNE THIS CITY.
- Behemoth: INDEED. THE
DISTORTION IS UNUSUALLY LARGE.
- Khamsin: WELL, WE SHOULD
MARK THIS AREA AS WELL.
- ( grunts )
JUST A FEW MORE AND WE SHOULD
HAVE ENOUGH FOR THE TUNING.
HOWEVER, I'M SENSING
SOMETHING STRANGE HERE,
AND IT'S NOT THE DISTORTION.
- Behemoth: HMM.
- ( Professor chuckling )
THINGS ARE PROGRESSING
RATHER NICELY.
IN FACT, I'D SAY
THEY'RE JUST PERFECT.
DO YOU CONCUR, DOMINO?
- Domino: ABSOLUTELY,
SIX HOURS 14 MINUTES
AND 32 SECONDS
UNTIL PREPARATIONS ARE COMPLETE!
- OH WHAT A GRAND
TIME WE'LL HAVE.
- JUST AS I THOUGHT,
THIS PATTERN REALLY SUITS YOU.
YU-CHAN IS GOING TO STOP DEAD
IN HIS TRACKS
WHEN HE SEES HOW
PRETTY YOU LOOK.
BUT HE SEEMS TO BE
RUNNING A LITTLE LATE.
- Yuji: I THOUGHT I WAS READY
TO LEAVE THIS CITY,
BUT IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
WHAT? IT'S LATER THAN I THOUGHT.
- ( running footsteps )
- SORRY YOSHIDA,
DID YOU WAIT LONG?
- UH, NO, NOT AT ALL.
- SHALL WE GO?
- OKAY.
- I WONDER WHAT'S TAKING
YU-CHAN SO LONG.
HE TRAINS WITH YOU EVERY
SATURDAY AFTERNOON,
SO HE SHOULD HAVE
BEEN HOME EARLY THEN.
- I TOLD HIM WE'D TRAIN
IN THE EVENING TODAY.
- OH!
- IT'S OKAY, I DIDN'T TELL HIM
WE WERE GOING TO THE FESTIVAL.
- I SEE.
THEN IN THAT CASE,
MAYBE HE STOPPED OFF
SOMEWHERE ON HIS WAY HOME.
- STOPPED OFF SOMEWHERE?
- WHAT DO YOU SAY
THE TWO OF US GO OUT
AND LOOK FOR HIM, SHANA-CHAN.
HE COULD BE HANGING OUT WITH IKE
AND HIS FRIENDS AT THE FESTIVAL.
WE'LL LEAVE A NOTE EXPLAINING
WHERE WE ARE,
IN CASE HE COMES HOME.
- BUT...
- I IMAGINE YU-CHAN WOULD BE
EVEN MORE SURPRISED
IF WE JUST HAPPENED
TO RUN INTO HIM.
- HUH?
- RIGHT?
- WHOA.
- LOOK OVER THERE, SHANA-CHAN,
THEY HAVE CANDY APPLES.
YU-CHAN ALWAYS HAS ONE WHEN
HE COMES TO THE FESTIVAL.
- WANNA TRY ONE?
- OKAY.
- SOMETHING WRONG?
DO YOU SEE HIM?
- NO, IT'S SOMEONE ELSE,
BUT IT'S OKAY.
- Tanaka: PLEASE, BIG SISTER,
YOU'RE INTERRUPTING
OUR TRAINING.
THIS ISN'T THE TIME TO
COME TO A FESTIVAL.
- Margery: OH, SHUT UP.
WHEN A WOMAN SAYS SHE
WANTS TO GO OUT,
IT'S A MAN'S JOB
TO ACCOMPANY HER.
- Marco: ALSO, ANY
MORE TRAINING
AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ENDED UP
TURNING EACH OTHER
INTO PLATES OF HUMAN SASHIMI.
- ( Marco laughs )
- Margery: EITA, BUY ME
SOMETHING WITH ALCOHOL.
- WHAT, YOU'RE GONNA DRINK?
- IS THAT GONNA BE A PROBLEM?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
- GOOD.
- OGA-CHAN, LET'S GO.
- RIGHT.
- Yuji: WOW, LOOK
AT ALL THE BOOTHS.
HEY, KEEP AN EYE OUT
FOR CANDY APPLES.
- I DO WANNA FIND OUT
IF SAKAI'S ALRIGHT,
BUT I'M AFRAID.
BUT I THINK NOT KNOWING
IS EVEN WORSE.
- WELL, I SUPPOSE ALL WE CAN DO
NOW IS WAIT FOR THAT GIRL
TO COOPERATE WITH US.
- Behemoth: HMM,
BUT THIS ODD FEELING
CONCERNS ME.
IT MIGHT BE BECAUSE OF
THE DISTORTION.
- THERE ARE NO INDICATIONS
OF ANY DENIZENS PRESENT.
AND THERE'S NOTHING WE
CAN DO ABOUT IT ANYWAY.
- Behemoth: HMM.
- Professor: YOU KNOW,
HUMANS ARE SO EASY
TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF.
ALL OF THOSE FLAME HAZES,
AND NOT EVEN ONE OF THEM
HAS DETECTED US.
- Domino: PROFESSOR,
PREPARATIONS ARE COMPLETE!
- EXCELLENT!
- HE'S FINE.
I'M SURE HE'S JUST FINE.
AND THEN, I'M GONNA
TELL HIM THAT I LOVE HIM.
- START THE EXPERIMENT!
- Domino: OKIE DOKIE!
- ( gasps )
- BUT HOW?
I DIDN'T SENSE IT UNTIL
RIGHT THIS MOMENT.
- Chigusa: SHANA-CHAN,
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- I FORGOT THERE'S
SOMETHING I HAVE TO DO.
PLEASE, GO ON WITHOUT ME.
PLEASE, GO ON.
- IS IT A DENIZEN?
- Marco: SEEMS THAT WAY, BUT
HOW COME WE'RE ONLY SENSING
THE UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM?
- IT MUST BE OFF,
HIDING SOMEWHERE.
ANYWAY, THE FESTIVITIES
ARE OVER FOR US.
- I GUESS THAT MEANS WE SHOULD
HEAD OVER TO THE CRYSTAL ALTAR.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO FIND
THAT DENIZON FOR YOU, RIGHT?
- Marco: IT'S BECOMING SECOND
NATURE TO YOU GUYS.
- YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO
WHEN YOU GET THERE, RIGHT?
- Sato: YOU BET.
- Tanaka: YOU BET.
- Marco: HEY, YOU'RE NOT
ACTUALLY THINKING
ABOUT BRINGING THEM
ALONG, ARE YOU?
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
I'M JUST TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
THEM WHILE I CAN, LIKE ALWAYS.
- WE NEED THE CRYSTAL
ALTAR FOR THE SEARCH.
- Marco: IN THAT CASE, ALRIGHT.
- WE'RE DEALING WITH AN
UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM
HERE THAT'S
VERY SOPHISTICATED.
- Alastor: IT WAS CLEARLY
FASHIONED BY SOMEONE
OF GREAT SKILL.
- YUJI MUST'VE SEEN IT BY NOW.
WHERE IS HE?
- A DENIZEN!
I HAVE TO FIND SHANA.
HEY YOSHIDA?
YOSHIDA, ARE YOU...
- HE CAN'T BE.
- NOT SAKAI.
- YOSHIDA, WHAT'S WRONG?
THIS IS A TREASURE. OH NO!
- YUJI!
KAZUMI YOSHIDA.
WHY? WHY WOULD SHE BE WITH YUJI?
IT CAN'T BE.
IT CAN'T!
- HEY, YOSHIDA!
- ( groans )
- SHANA?
- WHY WAS SHE HERE, YUJI?
- LISTEN, I THINK THAT YOSHIDA
FOUND OUT THAT I'M A TORCH.
I HAVE TO GO AFTER HER.
SHE WAS UPSET AND CRYING.
I CAN'T LEAVE HER LIKE THIS.
- WHY CAN'T YOU JUST IGNORE HER?
- IGNORE HER?
- SHANA.
- JUST IGNORE HER!
ARE YOU BLIND? THERE'S A
DENIZEN ON THE LOOSE HERE.
- I KNOW, BUT...
I HAVE TO GO AND
TALK TO HER PROPERLY.
- NO, YOU HAVE TO
BE WITH ME, YUJI.
FORGET ABOUT TALKING
TO KAZUMI YOSHIDA.
- IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
- STOP IT, LEAVE HER ALONE!
SHE HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH US!
- NOTHING TO DO WITH...
- YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE.
KAZUMI YOSHIDA HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH US.
SHE DOESN'T MATTER TO US.
- SHANA!
I NEVER EXPECTED YOU TO
SAY THOSE THINGS, SHANA.
WELL, SHE DOES MATTER TO ME.
- YUJI!
- YOSHIDA!
- YUJI.
- EXCUSE ME, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHERE DOES IT HURT?
- Alastor: SHANA.
- YUJI.
YUJI.
- Khamsin: LOOK AT IT.
OH, SO IT'S YOU I SEE.
- Alastor: MOBILIZER OF
CEREMONIAL EQUIPMENT,
IT WAS YOU TWO!
- Behemoth: IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
FLAME OF HEAVEN.
- WELL THEN, I TAKE IT YOU
HAVE SEEN THE SYSTEM.
- Margery: MARCOSIAS, I'M
GETTING A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS CRAZY SYSTEM.
- Marco: YEAH, IT'S DANTALIAN,
THE SEEKER.
THIS HAS TO BE THE WORK OF
THAT WHACKED OUT PROFESSOR.
BUT I HAVEN'T PICKED UP
HIS PRESENCE ANYWHERE.
- ANOTHER REASON WHY WE
NEED THE CRYSTAL ALTAR.
KEISAKU, EITA, HURRY UP.
- WHERE THE HELL DID TANAKA
GET TO? IS HE LOST?
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING, OGA-CHAN?
- PLEASE, I'M IN A HURRY.
- FORGET IT, NOT UNTIL YOU TELL
ME ALL ABOUT THAT WOMAN
YOU WERE
HANGING AROUND WITH.
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
SHE'S AN ACQUAINTANCE.
- IS THAT THE TRUTH?
- YES.
AND I REALLY AM IN A HURRY.
LET ME GO.
- YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT.
YOU'RE LYING TO ME.
- WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE REALLY
STARTING TO GET ON MY NERVES.
WHAT GIVES YOU THE RIGHT
TO ASK ME THIS STUFF?
- BECAUSE,
I FEEL, A LITTLE JEALOUS.
- WHATEVER, LOOK I
HAVE TO GET GOING.
- SHE MAKES ME JEALOUS.
- WHAT?
- SHE MAKES ME REALLY JEALOUS.
- WHY WOULD YOU BE JEALOUS?
- SHE MAKES ME JEALOUS,
BECAUSE I'M IN LOVE WITH
YOU EITA TANAKA.
YOU GET IT NOW?
- UH...
- ( groans )
- SAKAI IS A TORCH.
HE'S DEAD.
- YOSHIDA. WHO WOULD'VE GIVEN
YOU SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
- Alastor: GATHER YOURSELF!
A DENIZEN HAS BEGUN HIS ATTACK.
- SORRY.
- LET'S GET BACK TO THE
MATTER AT HAND, SHALL WE?
THIS UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM
IS MAKING THINGS WORSE.
IF IT KEEPS UP, THE DISTORTION
WILL BE TOO LARGE TO REPAIR,
AND THE WHOLE CITY
WILL BE ENGULFED.
- Alastor: WHAT IS ITS PURPOSE?
IS THERE ANYTHING WE CAN DO?
- Khamsin: YES, WE NEED
TO BEGIN THE TUNING.
WE'VE ALREADY LAID DOWN
THE NECESSARY MARKINGS.
ALL WE NEED NOW IS THE HELP
OF A PERSON WHO HOLDS
THE TRUE IMAGE OF THE
CITY IN THEIR MIND.
- Behemoth: ACTUALLY, WE
DID FIND SOMEONE, BUT
WE'VE RUN INTO A BIT
OF A PROBLEM WITH HER.
A YOUNG WOMAN
NAMED KAZUMI YOSHIDA.
- OH, I TAKE IT YOU KNOW HER.
AH, YOU MUST BE THE CAUSE
OF THE STRANGE FEELING
I PICKED UP FROM HER.
AS SOON AS SHE SHOWS UP, WE CAN
BEGIN THE ACTUAL TUNING PROCESS.
- AS YOU WISH,
I'LL GO AND BRING HER HERE.
- Alastor: WILL YOU BE OKAY?
- I'LL BE FINE.
I WILL FULFILL MY MISSION
AS A FLAME HAZE.
IT HURTS.
- Professor: RIGHT ABOUT NOW IS
WHEN THE FLAME HAZES
START MEDDLING
WITH MY PLANS.
OH DOMINO,
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO NEXT!
- Domino: YES! IT'S TIME TO
BEGIN THE SECOND PHASE!
- ( people screaming )
- BE SEALED!
- OGA-CHAN.
- I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T EXPECT THAT.
I CAN'T GIVE YOU AN
ANSWER RIGHT NOW,
BUT I'LL COME BACK LATER
AND TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- SATO! HOW CAN HE MOVE
AROUND INSIDE THE SEAL?
THIS IS BAD. I'VE GOTTA
DO SOMETHING, ANYTHING.
CAN I DO THIS?
- ( screams )
- YUKARI?
- SAKAI?
- SATO, QUICK! THIS WAY!
- SAKAI, BUT HOW?
- IT TOOK A WHILE, BUT THINGS
ARE STARTING TO GET EXCITING!
YOU CAN'T WAIT TO SEE WHAT
THRILLING EVENT
TAKES PLACE NEXT, NOW CAN YOU?
- Domino: YOU GOT THAT
RIGHT, PROFESSOR!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE PROFESSOR GOES
UNDETECTED AS THE WHOLE SACRED
CHAPEL NEARS COMPLETION
OVER MISAKI CITY.
SHANA FIGHTS AS A FLAME HAZE,
BUT SHE CAN FEEL YUJI
SLIPPING AWAY FROM HER.
NEXT EPISODE,
"WITHIN THE BATTLE."