- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- YOU'RE ONE OF THEM.
- THAT'S RIGHT. I AM
CALLED A FLAME HAZE.
MY TASK IN THIS WORLD IS
TO FIGHT THE DENIZENS.
- Khamsin: SEE HOW
THE WORLD REALLY IS.
- I CAN'T TAKE THIS.
IT'S TOO MUCH.
- YUJI.
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- Alastor: SHANA.
- ( gasps )
- IT APPEARS YOUR HELP IS NEEDED
TO FIX THIS CITY'S DISTORTION.
COME WITH ME, QUICKLY.
- ( panting )
- THEN YOU'RE THE MYSTES
MARGERY'S BEEN TALKING ABOUT.
- YEAH.
- AND YOU. YOU'RE WITH
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- RIGHT, TANAKA TOO.
- I SEE. SURPRISING.
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I WAS THINKING.
IF YOU REALLY ARE A MYSTES,
THEN THE REAL YUJI SAKAI...
- YUJI SAKAI IS DEAD.
THAT'S RIGHT. I'M DEAD.
- YOU'RE... YOU'RE PRETTY TOUGH.
- YEAH, YOU THINK SO?
- NOT TOO MANY PEOPLE COULD
STAY CALM. YOU'VE GOT GUTS.
- I'M NOT LIKE THAT.
I'VE ALWAYS WORRIED ABOUT
HOW PEOPLE WOULD REACT
IF THEY FOUND OUT THE TRUTH.
TONIGHT FOR INSTANCE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'VE GOTTA GO FIND YOSHIDA.
- YOSHIDA?
- SHE FOUND OUT
THAT I'M A TORCH.
SHE WAS COMPLETELY
SHOCKED BY IT.
I NEED TO EXPLAIN ALL OF THIS.
THOUGH I GUESS THAT
WON'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
A FACT IS A FACT.
- ( loud screeching sound )
- ( gasps )
- Professor: ( laughing )
DOMINO,
I CAN SEE THE WHOLE SACRED
CHAPEL RISING BEFORE ME.
CAN I ASSUME IT'S ALMOST
FULLY OPERATIONAL?
- Domino: INDEED,
YOUR ASSUMPTION IS
CORRECT, PROFESSOR!
AT THIS POINT, I AM PLEASED TO
REPORT THE FLAME HAZES
SEEM TO HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NO IDEA WHAT IT IS.
- YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
ITS PURPOSE IS TO ACTUALLY
INCREASE THE DISTORTION.
MORE LIKELY THAN NOT,
THE DISTORTION
IS MERELY A SIDE EFFECT
FROM ITS OTHER OPERATION.
- Behemoth: THE SEEKER DOES
HAVE A REPUTATION
FOR DOING UNNECESSARY THINGS.
- WE'LL JUST OBSERVE FOR NOW.
- DAMMIT, HOW MUCH LONGER DO I
HAVE TO DEAL WITH THESE PESTS?
AND WHY HAVEN'T KEISAKU AND EITA
REACHED THE CRYSTAL ALTAR YET?
- Marco:
I'M NOT PICKING UP ANYTHING
FROM THAT WHACKED OUT
CRAZY PROFESSOR.
HE'S NOT SHY ABOUT MOVING
HIS RINNE ALL OVER THE PLACE.
- NOW WHAT?
- Marco: THAT REMINDS ME,
THERE'S ANOTHER FLAME
HAZE IN THE MIX.
- I WONDER IF HE HAS SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THE SEEKER.
- Marco: WHY DON'T WE FIND HIM
AND PUT HIM ON THE SPOT?
- SOUNDS GOOD.
THEN SHALL WE GO?
- Marco: CLIMB ON!
- WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
- THESE RINNES DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH THEM,
AND NEITHER DOES SHANA.
IT'S THE OTHER FLAME HAZE.
MARGERY SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT ANOTHER ONE
SHOWING UP IN THE CITY.
- IT'S HIS! THIS IS HIS!
THIS THING SHOWED
EVERYTHING TO YOSHIDA.
- SAKAI, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WAIT, I'VE GOTTA GET
TO THE CRYSTAL ALTAR.
HE'S A TORCH.
- YUKARI IS A FLAME HAZE?
THEN SHE KNOWS ABOUT EVERYTHING
HAPPENING IN THIS CITY...
AND ABOUT SAKAI.
SHE KNOWS EVERYTHING,
AND YET SHE STILL...
- ( exclaims )
AND YET SHE STILL CARES FOR HIM.
- LET'S GO.
- I'M FINE. I CAN KEEP UP.
- GOOD.
- I CAN KEEP UP.
- AH, IT'S CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
SO, YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO WAS FIGHTING.
- Behemoth: HMM, SO EXPLAINS THE
AGGRESSIVE PRESENCE WE SENSED.
- OH, IT'S ONLY YOU TWO GEEZERS.
HOW BORING.
- Marco: YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THAT CRACKPOT PROFESSOR.
- Behemoth: HMM,
I TAKE IT YOU'RE JUST
AS PUZZLED AS WE ARE
OVER NOT BEING ABLE TO
DETECT THE SEEKER.
- OF COURSE.
HE MUST BE USING
SOME KIND OF TRICK.
- BUT WHAT?
- WE ARE TRYING TO FIGURE...
OH, WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
- SEEMS TO BE A MYSTES.
- HE'S NOT INVOLVED.
DON'T WORRY.
- Marco: HE LOOKS PRETTY
MAD FOR SOME REASON.
- THIS BELONG TO YOU?
- YES.
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN,
YOU ARE YUJI SAKAI.
- Behemoth: HMM.
WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT
YOU'D END UP BEING A MYSTES?
I FEEL BAD FOR WHAT THAT YOUNG
LADY HAD TO GO THROUGH.
- WHY? WHY DID YOU HAVE
TO GET HER INVOLVED?
- WE NEED SOMEONE
TO COOPERATE WITH US,
AND SHE WAS THE BEST QUALIFIED.
- QUALIFIED? YOU GAVE
HER THIS TREASURE
BASED ON THAT KIND OF NONSENSE?
- YUJI.
- SAKAI!
- CAN YOU IMAGINE HOW
SHOCKED SHE MUST HAVE BEEN
WHEN SHE SAW HOW THE
WORLD REALLY LOOKED?
SHE DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT ALL OF THIS,
SO WHY DID YOU HAVE TO
DRAG HER INTO THIS WORLD?
WHY? WHY!
- BE CALM.
I CAN SEE THAT SHE IS A VERY
IMPORTANT PERSON TO YOU.
- YOSHIDA'S A PERSON
OF GREAT KINDNESS.
SHE WASN'T SUPPOSED TO
COME TO THIS WORLD.
SHE SHOULD HAVE STAYED BEHIND
IN THE WORLD I CAN'T GO BACK TO.
- SAKAI.
- HUH?
YOSHIDA.
SORRY FOR EVERYTHING.
- OH, YUJI.
- ALRIGHT, WE'RE VERY TOUCHED.
THAT WAS A BEAUTIFUL SCENE,
BUT LET'S TRY TO FOCUS
ON REALITY, SHALL WE?
- YES, SHE'S RIGHT.
I THINK I'VE GOT A GRASP ON THE
SITUATION WITH THIS SYSTEM.
- Alastor: SHANA!
- KAZUMI YOSHIDA HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH US!
- THAT WASN'T LIKE SHANA.
WHY'D SHE SAY THAT?
- ABOUT THE
UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM...
IT'S GOING TO OPEN
A HOLE IN SPACE
BY UTILIZING THE
CITY'S DISTORTION.
- A HOLE IN SPACE?
- YES.
AS IF YOU TOOK A PIECE
OUT OF A JIGSAW PUZZLE.
THAT'S WHAT IT WOULD LOOK LIKE.
- Marco: SURE, BUT WHY?
- Alastor: WHAT MEANING IS THERE
IN DOING SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- Behemoth: HMM, THE SEEKER HAS
ALWAYS DONE THINGS
THAT SIMPLY DON'T
MAKE MUCH SENSE.
- IN ANY CASE, IT'S CLEAR THE
CITY IS BEING AFFECTED BY IT.
WE SHOULD BEGIN THE TUNING
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
AS I EXPLAINED YESTERDAY,
WE'D LIKE YOU TO
COOPERATE WITH US.
- WHAT? COOPERATE?
IT'S NOT FAIR TO
INVOLVE HER IN THIS.
- UNLESS WE ACT, THIS CITY
IS ONLY GONNA GET WORSE.
- SAKAI, IT'S OKAY.
I MADE A PROMISE TO KHAMSIN.
AND I'M JUST FINE NOW.
I'M SORRY FOR
RUNNING OFF BEFORE.
- YOSHIDA...
- COME HERE PLEASE.
VENTRICLE OF KEDESH.
- Marco: HEY,
NOTHING'S HAPPENING!
- YES.
- WE SEEM TO HAVE A PROBLEM.
- Behemoth: HMM.
THAT UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM IS
PREVENTING THE NUMEROUS MARKINGS
WE PLACED IN THE
CITY FROM MOVING.
- ALL THAT TO NOW YOU SAY
YOU CAN'T DO YOUR TUNING?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- JUST A MINUTE.
- Tanaka: BIG SISTER,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- SURE CAN.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
- Tanaka: SORRY, I WAS HELD UP.
- Margery: FORGET THAT.
IS THE CRYSTAL ALTAR WORKING?
- UH, JUST A MOMENT.
UM, THERE'S A HOLE
AT THE TOP OF THAT
UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM
ABOVE THE CITY.
- Margery: WE KNOW ABOUT THAT.
ANYTHING ELSE?
- THE SYSTEM IS SPREAD
ACROSS THE CITY,
BUT THE LINES LEAD TO
A SINGLE LOCATION.
- Margery: WHERE?
- THE RIVERBANK.
MAYBE THE FESTIVAL'S
MAIN STAGE.
- THE FESTIVAL'S MAIN
STAGE DOWN BY THE RIVER.
HE SAYS THAT'S WHERE THE CORE
OF THE UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM IS.
- I BET IT'S THE TOWER!
- I DON'T SENSE ANYTHING.
- COME TO THINK OF IT,
THE SEEKER HAS A MECHANICAL
ASSISTANT WORKING FOR HIM.
A RINNE COMPRISED OF MACHINERY.
- IT'S CALLED DOMINO, RIGHT?
- Behemoth: HMM, I'D
FORGOTTEN ABOUT IT.
IT'S NOT SURPRISING WE WEREN'T
ABLE TO SENSE HIS ASSISTANT.
- I'M SURE DESTROYING THAT RINNE
WOULD AFFECT THE
UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM.
- HERE. USE THIS TO REACH ME,
JUST IN CASE.
- LET'S GO MARCOSIAS!
- Marco: TALLY-HO!
- Alastor: WE SHOULD GO AS WELL.
- Yuji: BE CAREFUL.
- USUALLY HE'D SAY HE
WAS COMING ALONG.
- Domino: PROFESSOR,
THE BASIC VALUE OF
THE WHOLE SACRED CHAPEL
IS NOW WITHIN
ESTIMATED RANGE.
THIS MEANS THE REQUIREMENT
FOR THE EXPERIMENT
HAVE ALL BEEN SATISFIED.
- Professor: EXCELLENT!
WHILE WE'RE AT IT, WE'LL
CONDUCT A TRIAL EXPERIMENT
USING A SIMPLE
UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM,
THAT I SO THOUGHTFULLY
BROUGHT ALONG.
- Domino: OH! DETECTING
INCOMING FLAME HAZES!
- Professor: I SUGGEST YOU
PREPARE YOURSELF,
AND DO SOMETHING ABOUT THEM.
I, ON THE OTHER HAND, WILL
PROCEED TO OUR RENDEZVOUS POINT.
THAT'S ALL. OVER AND OUT.
- THAT'S IT.
- ( grunting )
- Marco: HEY, HEY! ALREADY?
- HUH? WHAT JUST
HAPPENED THERE?
- Marco: THE RINNE!
- Margery: I SEE.
DEFENSIVE UNRESTRICTED
METHODS ARE BEING USED
TO DEFLECT POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- ( Domino laughs )
YOUR ATTACKS ARE
INEFFECTIVE AGAINST ME!
BEGIN TRANSFORMATION!
- Marco: IS THERE A
POINT TO ALL THIS?
- I DON'T KNOW, BUT THAT
DEFLECTION EARLIER
HAS ME A BIT WORRIED.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS TO APPROACH.
THERE'S THE LUNATIC NOW.
HE'S MAKING HIS MOVE.
- HE WAS OUTSIDE THE CITY.
- YES,
HE WASN'T ACTUALLY
HIDING FROM US AT ALL.
THAT'S WHY WE WEREN'T
ABLE TO DETECT HIM.
- Behemoth: HMM, BUT HOW IS HE
PLANNING ON ENTERING THE CITY?
- THERE'S NO DOUBT.
HE IS COMING CLOSER.
- THAT'S IT!
- WELL, I'M ARRIVING
IN STYLE.
- ( maniacal laughter )
- AN AIRSHIP?
- Khamsin: THE SEEKER LOVES TO
BE SHOWY FOR NO REAL REASON.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF
THERE'S NO MEANING
TO HIS PLAN AT ALL.
- HANG ON A SECOND.
- WHAT IS IT?
- THERE COULD BE A REASON WHY HE
CHOSE TO COME IN FROM THE AIR.
YOU SAID SOMETHING
EARLIER ABOUT REMOVING
A JIGSAW PIECE FROM SPACE.
- Khamsin: YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
- ANY CHANCE THAT AIRSHIP
IS THE FINAL PIECE?
- YOU KNOW, THE BOY'S
THEORY HAS MERIT.
- I THINK YOU SHOULD
HEAD TO THAT SPACE
AND FORGET ABOUT THE ROBOT.
- I BET THE AIRSHIP IS
PROTECTED WITH THE SAME
KIND OF DEFENSE MECHANISM.
ATTACKING IT ISN'T
GOING TO WORK.
- BUT IF MY THEORY'S CORRECT,
ANY DEFENSIVE MEASURES
WILL BE AFFECTED
BY THE SYSTEM THAT
MADE THE HOLE.
WHICH WOULD MEAN...
- Margery: THE MECHANISM WOULD
HAVE TO BE DEACTIVATED
TO GET NEAR THE SPACE.
- RIGHT.
- SAKAI IS INCREDIBLE.
- AND IF NEEDED, I WILL STAGE
AN ATTACK ON THE AIRSHIP MYSELF.
- Marco: IS HE SERIOUS?
- I SINCERELY HOPE HE
DOESN'T DO THAT.
- I CAN'T HEAR YUJI'S VOICE.
HE'S SO FAR AWAY.
- OKAY, I'M FINISHED
TRANSFORMING NOW.
FLAME HAZES COME AT ME!
THERE'S NO ONE THERE.
- LO, BEHOLD! THE CLIMAX
AND THE GRAND FINALE!
BEGIN THE EXPERIMENT! DEACTIVATE
THE UNRESTRICTED METHOD!
- ( screaming )
- Margery: RIDE A COCK
HORSE TO BANBURY CROSS.
SHE SHALL HAVE MUSIC
WHEREVER SHE GOES!
- WEIRD FLAME HAZES!
- HE'S STILL NUTTY
AS A FRUITCAKE.
- Shana: WE CAN'T LET
HIM GET AWAY WITH THIS.
- DAMN THEM!
I'M BEING THWARTED BY
WRONG-HEADED THINKERS
WHO REFUSE TO BE ENLIGHTENED!
- DOMINO!
- Domino: YESSIREE!
- IT'S TIME TO USE THE SPECIAL
TECHNIQUE WE PREPARED
IN CASE THINGS WENT AWRY.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- Marco: THIS IS GETTING
TOO SILLY FOR ME.
- I GUESS HE WANTED TO TRY IT.
- ( laughing ) THIS BRILLIANT
MANEUVER HERALDS THE END!
- Khamsin: PLEASE GET OUT OF
THE WAY. I'LL FINISH HIM OFF.
- YOU WILL?
- THE OLD MAN'S GONNA OPEN FIRE!
- Marco: RUN FOR IT!
- WHAT?
- Alastor: MOVE! NOW!
- HAVE I WON THE FIGHT ALREADY?
- ( screams )
- Domino:
PERHAPS IT WAS POINTLESS
TO COMBINE LIKE THAT. OW. OW.
- I DECIDE WHETHER SOMETHING
IS POINTLESS OR NOT!
ESCAPE!
- WHAT IN THE WORLD DID
HE COME HERE FOR?
- Marco: I DON'T
EVEN WANNA KNOW.
- YOSHIDA, ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
- YES.
- UH, SORRY.
- UH, YOSHIDA?
- SAKAI, YOU'RE SO WARM.
ARE YOU EVER GONNA GET BETTER?
- NO.
THE REAL ME IS ALREADY DEAD.
THE ME RIGHT HERE
ISN'T EVEN HUMAN.
- NO, SAKAI, YOU'RE HUMAN.
I KNOW IT FOR A FACT.
- HUMAN? BUT WHY?
- BECAUSE YOU'RE SO WARM.
YOUR BODY AND YOUR HEART.
- THAT MAKES ME HUMAN?
- MMM-HMM. THAT'S WHAT I LIKE
ABOUT YOU
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
I, I LOVE YOU, SAKAI.
- NOW, THE VENTRICLE OF KEDESH.
YOUNG LADY,
PLEASE IMAGINE THE
CITY AS YOU KNOW IT.
THAT IMAGE WILL CORRECT
THE DISTORTION
AND FINE TUNE THE PROCESS.
- OKAY.
MY CITY.
- I FEEL IT.
IT'S THE CITY, THE ONE I'VE
LIVED IN EVER SINCE I WAS BORN.
- Behemoth: HMM, THIS IS GOOD.
THE IMAGES ARE VERY WARM.
- I LIVED HERE.
- Yoshida: NO, SAKAI,
YOU'RE HUMAN.
- ( crying )
- I CAN TELL. YUJI.
YUJI'S NOT GONNA COME WITH ME.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
- ( panting )
- WHAT SEEMS TO
BE BOTHERING YOU?
- WIRHELMINA.
- I THOUGHT I WARNED YOU
NOT TO OVERDO THINGS.
AH, SEEKER. YOU WERE ONLY
RESPONSIBLE FOR PREPARATIONS.
- WELL, THE EXPERIMENT ACHIEVED
FULL RESULTS, DIDN'T IT?
I REALLY DON'T APPRECIATE YOU
NAGGING ME FOR SUCCESS.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
EVERYTHING'S GOING SO WELL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: IT'S BEEN A WHILE SINCE
SHANA LAST SAW HER OLD TEACHER.
BUT WIRHELMINA IS SENSING
SOME CHANGES IN HER.
AND THEN, SHE GIVES
SHANA AN ULTIMATUM.
NEXT EPISODE,
"HEARTLESS WIRHELMINA."