- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED
AND THE FLAMES OF THE CRIMSON
WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: I KNEW I WAS GOING
TO LEAVE THIS WORLD
BEFORE TOO LONG.
BUT I ALSO KNEW
THAT I WAS YUJI SAKAI.
AND EVEN THOUGH ONE DAY
NO ONE WILL REMEMBER ME,
THE POWER OF MY EXISTENCE
HELPED SAVE IKE AND THE OTHERS.
I WAS SATISFIED WITH THAT.
AND I WAS GLAD I COULD DO
SOME GOOD BEFORE I DISAPPEARED.
I THOUGHT I UNDERSTOOD
WHAT WAS GOING ON,
BUT THE TRUTH WAS...
I DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING.
EVERYTHING WAS JUST BEGINNING,
INCLUDING MY TIES WITH SHANA.
- ( dog barking )
- LET'S SEE.
WHERE ARE
THOSE COFFEE SPOONS?
- Shana: THAT TORCH'S FLAME
WAS ABOUT TO GO OUT,
BUT THEN IT RECOVERED.
HOW?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- Alastor: HMM.
IT MAY HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE TREASURE INSIDE.
- SO WHAT KIND OF TREASURE?
YOU DON'T MEAN--
- THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- IS THAT POSSIBLE?
- I AGREE.
IT IS INCREDIBLE THAT SOMETHING
OF SUCH VALUE WOULD JUST APPEAR.
- HMM.
- BUT IF TRUE,
THEN IT'S EVEN MORE REASON
WHY WE CANNOT
LET THE HUNTER ACQUIRE IT.
WE'LL NEED TO BE WATCHFUL
AS EVENTS UNFOLD.
- HMM.
- SORRY ABOUT THE WAIT.
HERE.  WHAT?
- UH, NOTHING.
- HUH?
AH.
IT'S STARTING TO RAIN.
- I CAN SEE THAT.
- WANNA COME INSIDE?
- HUH?  THE HOUSE?
- YEAH.
YOU'RE GONNA GET SOAKED.
FIRST OF ALL,
IF YOU'RE WATCHING OVER ME,
I THINK YOU'D WANNA BE
BY MY SIDE.
- TRUE.
- DOESN'T THAT MAKE SENSE?
- IT'S NOT SOMETHING
YOU NEED TO BRAG ABOUT.
- I WASN'T BRAGGING ABOUT IT.
I WAS JUST WONDERING.
- FLAME HAZES ARE NOT BOTHERED
BY WEATHER CONDITIONS.
- OKAY, LET'S GO.
- SURE, OKAY.
MY MOM'S SLEEPING
ON THE MAIN FLOOR,
SO JUST DON'T MAKE
ANY LOUD NOISES.
- ( springs creak )
- YOU'LL USE THAT BED.
I'M GONNA GO SLEEP
IN MY DAD'S STUDY.
- HEY, IF I CAME IN HERE
TO GUARD YOU,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
SLEEPING IN ANOTHER ROOM?
- UH, BECAUSE.
- Alastor:
THIS WAS YOUR SUGGESTION.
SLEEP HERE.
- UH, HMM?
AH! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M GETTING CHANGED,
OBVIOUSLY.
- SURE, BUT, UH, LOOK--
IS THERE SOME PLACE YOU--
- WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
SO RATTLED ABOUT?
YOU'VE NOTHING TO FEAR.
- HIDE WHILE I CHANGE.
- UH, OKAY.
- DON'T PEEK
OR I'LL CLOBBER YOU.
- MAN, YOU'RE TESTY.
- I SAID MOVE!
- DON'T RUSH ME.
IT'S SOMETHING I DIDN'T EXPECT.
- WHAT IS?
- I THINK YOU'RE
EMBARRASSED ABOUT THIS TOO.
AAH!
- ( grunts )
- ( sighs ) HMM.
NO P.J.s?
- ( object clattering )
- I TOLD YOU, NO PEEKING!
- I WASN'T.
I WAS JUST ASKING
IF YOU HAVE ANY PAJAMAS.
- WELL, I DON'T.
JUST MY UNDERCLOTHES.
ALASTOR CLEANS MY BODY
WITH HIS FLAME
SO I DON'T HAVE TO CHANGE
VERY OFTEN.
- WOW, THAT SOUNDS CONVENIENT.
OH, I HAVE A JERSEY
IN THAT DRAWER BESIDE MY BED.
YOU CAN USE THAT.
BY THE WAY, WHY DON'T
YOU HAVE ANY BAGS?
- ALMOST EVERYTHING
I HAVE IS WITH ME.
- WHERE?
- MY NIGHT CAPE-- A BLACK CAPE
ESPECIALLY FOR FLAME HAZES.
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE MAGIC.
- YEAH, THANK ALASTOR FOR THAT.
- AH.  THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
SO WHAT KIND OF PERSON
IS ALASTOR?
- I AM NOT HUMAN.  I AM A LORD
OF THE CRIMSON WORLD.
- WHAT?  YOU'RE ONE
OF THOSE DENIZENS?
THE THINGS THAT SUCK UP
EXISTENCES?
- THERE ARE THOSE WHO CONSUME
EXISTENCE WITHOUT RESTRAINT,
AND THEN THERE ARE THOSE
LIKE ME, WHO OPPOSE THEM.
THIS WORLD IS FILLED
WITH THE POWER OF EXISTENCE,
SOMETHING THE CRIMSON WORLD
LACKS.
THAT IS WHY THE DENIZENS
ARE DRAWN HERE.
THEY SEEK OUT THIS POWER
BECAUSE IT CAN BE USED
TO FULFILL THEIR DESIRES.
- AH, AND SO WHERE
DO THESE DENIZENS COME FROM?
- Shana: FROM THE CRIMSON WORLD,
THE WORLD NEXT TO THIS ONE
THAT CANNOT BE REACHED
BY ORDINARY MEANS.
- LIKE A DIFFERENT DIMENSION?
- Alastor:
AS GOOD A DEFINITION AS ANY.
BUT TOYING WITH THE POWER
OF EXISTENCE
WILL EVENTUALLY UPSET THE
BALANCE BETWEEN THE TWO WORLDS.
THUS,
THE NEED FOR FLAME HAZES.
IT IS OUR TASK TO PREVENT THIS
FROM HAPPENING.
- IT SOUNDS LIKE THERE ARE MORE
THAN JUST YOU TWO OUT THERE.
- THERE ARE OTHER FLAME HAZES,
BUT WE'RE ALL ON OUR OWN.
- Alastor: THEIR REASONS FOR
FIGHTING AND METHODS VARY
FROM ONE TO THE OTHER.
THERE ARE EVEN TIMES
WHEN FLAME HAZES
WILL BATTLE EACH OTHER.
SOME OF THEM
ARE EASILY AGITATED.
- OH.
I THINK IT WOULD MAKE MORE SENSE
IF EVERYONE COOPERATED.
OW.
( grunting )
AAH!
OW!  HMM?
- ( gasps )
- UH, UH, UH...
- ( punching sounds,
pan clanging )
- YU-CHAN,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- NOTHING.
I'M JUST CLEANING MY ROOM.
- AH.  WELL, IT'S LATE,
SO DO IT QUICKLY.
- YEAH, GOTCHA.
( laughs )
- ( door closes )
- AH.
- UGH!  I SHOULD HAVE
PUNCHED HIM ANOTHER 10 TIMES.
- Alastor: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT'S ONLY A TORCH.
- YOUR POINT?
- WOULD YOU BE EMBARRASSED
TO BE NAKED
IN FRONT OF A ROCK OR A TREE?
THIS IS OUT OF CHARACTER
FOR YOU.
- LOOK,
I JUST FELT UNCOMFORTABLE.
- HMM.
- ( gasps )
YOU FEEL IT?
- YES.  A FLAME HAZE.
- DO YOU THINK
IT'S HERE AFTER FRIAGNE?
- EVEN IF IT IS,
I'M SURE IT WILL LEAVE
WHEN IT FINDS OUT
THAT WE WERE HERE FIRST.
AFTER ALL, IT IS WELL KNOWN
THAT ENCOUNTERS
BETWEEN FLAME HAZES
NEVER TURN OUT WELL.
- MMM.
- ( footsteps echoing )
- AAH!
- ( stuttering )
- YOUR BEST ROOM, AND DON'T
TELL ME IT'S NOT AVAILABLE.
- YE-- YES, MA'AM.
- ( door rattling )
- OH, COME ON.
THIS IS THE BEST ROOM
IN THE CITY?
I'M SO GRATEFUL
I COULD WEEP.
- Marco: OH-HO-HO!
WHY NOT CHARM SOME YOUNG STUD
INTO GIVING YOU A NICE PLACE
TO SLEEP AGAIN, EH?  EH?
MY DEAR MISTRESS,
PRINCESS MARGERY DAW.
( laughing )
- QUIET, STUPID MARCO.
- ( Marco laughing )
OH!
- DAMN.
WHAT AN ABSURD LITTLE CITY
TO WANDER INTO.
THAT CORPSE-COLLECTING
BASTARD!
THERE'S A DENIZEN AS WELL AS
ANOTHER FLAME HAZE IN THIS DIVE,
AND SIMPLY SCADS OF TORCHES.
THEY'RE MAKING IT VERY DIFFICULT
TO SENSE WHERE HE IS.
- THEN WHY DON'T YOU DEAL
WITH THE DENIZEN
OR THE FLAME HAZE FIRST?
SMASH THEM!  BURN THEM!
- THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
THIS PLACE IS A JOKE.
THESE BOTTLES ARE TINY.
AND IT'S NOTHING
BUT CHEAP BOOZE.
- ( laughing )
THIS IS A WONDERFUL HOTEL.
IF YOU DON'T DRINK,
YOU DON'T SNORE,
WHICH MEANS I'LL ACTUALLY
BE ABLE TO GET SOME SLEEP!
OW!
- Friagne: I FEEL IT.
IT'S A FLAME HAZE.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS MEANS
I'LL HAVE TO POSTPONE
MY HUNT FOR THAT MYSTES.
- Marianne:
MASTER, ANOTHER FLAME HAZE.
AS IF THAT ONE WITH
THE FIERY HAIR WASN'T ENOUGH!
- CALM YOURSELF, MARIANNE.
I'VE ALMOST ACQUIRED ENOUGH
OF THE POWER I NEED FOR YOU.
I WON'T LET ANYONE
INTERFERE WITH THE PLAN.
WHEN ALL THIS IS OVER, YOU NO
LONGER WILL BE A MERE RINNE.
YOU WILL BE AN EXISTENCE
AND WILL LIVE IN THE WORLD
AS YOU DESERVE.
- YOU HAVE ALREADY DONE
SO MUCH FOR ME, MASTER.
- NO, IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
IF NOT FOR MY POWERS,
YOU WOULD VANISH
IN A MATTER OF DAYS.
THAT'S TOO TRANSIENT
TO BE A REAL EXISTENCE.
- I THINK YOU AND I
SHARE A SPECIAL BOND,
ONE THAT CAN'T BE DEFINED
BY WORDS ALONE.
- AH.  OH, MARIANNE.
MARIANNE, YOU SAY
THE MOST WONDERFUL THINGS TO ME.
HOWEVER...
I MUST SEE THIS AFFAIR
THROUGH TO THE END.
THAT'S WHY I CAME HERE,
THE REASON
I PURSUE EXISTENCES.
I'M DOING IT FOR YOU.
EVERYTHING I DO
IS FOR YOUR SAKE.
OH, WHAT A SUBLIME SIGHT.
LOOK, SO MANY EXISTENCES
OUT THERE.
- MASTER.
- DON'T WORRY.
EVERYTHING IS GOING
TO BE JUST FINE.
- WHY?
MMM, I'M SLEEPY.
- Alastor: YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN GETTING MUCH REST LATELY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO INSIDE
THE HOUSE TO SLEEP.
- MMM, OKAY.
- ( birds chirping )
- AH.
MY PILLOW SMELLS NICE.
MMM.
HUH?  OH, IT'S ONLY YOU, SHANA.
HUH? ( gasps )
- ( muttering )
- AAH!
WHAT THE--
AAH!
- Alastor: I SEE YOU'RE AWAKE.
- WHAT IS SHE DOING IN MY BED?
- NOTHING FOR YOU
TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M STILL SHAKING.
- ( moans )
- AAH.
- HUH?
- AAH!
- HOW DARE YOU?!
- STOP!  WAIT!
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING, HONESTLY!
- Alastor:
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
YOU LOOKED TIRED, SO I SUGGESTED
YOU GO INTO THE HOUSE TO SLEEP.
IT WAS YOUR DECISION,
HALF ASLEEP, I MIGHT ADD,
TO CRAWL INTO HIS BED.
I DON'T SEE THE PROBLEM.
NORMALLY THIS
WOULDN'T BOTHER YOU.
- RIGHT.
THERE'S NO PROBLEM.
- HUH?
- BECAUSE YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A TORCH.
- AND THAT MAKES IT OKAY?
- SHUT UP!
SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
HMM!
- UH.
OKAY THEN,
LET'S GET READY FOR SCHOOL.
YOU GET CHANGED
WHILE I GO AND WASH UP, OKAY?
- HMM.
WHY?
- AH.
THIS IS CRAZY.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
HOW CUTE SHE WAS.
OH, JUST FORGET IT.
- HEY, YOU MAGGOTS!  LET'S SEE
SOME ENERGY OUT THERE.
- Girl:
WHAT THE HELL'S WRONG WITH HIM?
HE'S SURE WORKED UP
ABOUT SOMETHING.
- Girl #2: I DON'T KNOW.
KONDO'S ALWAYS BEEN KINDA WEIRD.
- I GUESS.
HE LOOKS LIKE A PERVERT.
- QUIET!
SAVE YOUR BREATH FOR RUNNING.
DAMN IT.
LOOK AT HER.
I BET SHE THINKS SHE'S SMART
MAKING FUN
OF THE OTHER TEACHERS.
SHE WON'T GET AWAY WITH THAT
IN MY CLASS.
I'LL TEACH HER A LESSON.
- WHAT IS THIS?
ARE WE GONNA RUN LAPS ALL DAY?
- YEAH, THERE'S SOMETHING
FUNNY HERE.
ONE GOOD THING--
AT LEAST SHE WON'T
BE GETTING INTO TROUBLE
WITH THE TEACHERS OUT HERE.
- HMM.  WHY?
- DAMN IT,
SHE HASN'T EVEN BROKEN A SWEAT.
WHY ISN'T THIS
GETTING TO HER?
- Boy: THAT ASSHOLE.
HE'S GETTING A KICK OUT OF THIS.
- Boy #2: THIS IS REALLY
PISSING ME OFF.
- AAH.
- YOSHIDA.
- KAZUMI!
- YOU!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- PLEASE, MR. KONDO,
YOU'VE GOT TO LET KAZUMI REST.
EVERYBODY KNOWS
THAT SHE'S ANEMIC.
- THAT'S JUST AN EXCUSE
TO SLACK OFF.
PHYSICAL FITNESS
DEMANDS EFFORT.
- MR. KONDO, THAT'S ENOUGH.
I THINK
THIS IS A LITTLE OVERBOARD.
- SAKAI, I'M DOING THIS
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD!
AAH!
- MOVE IT, JERK.
- WHY, YOU LITTLE THUG!
- THIS DRILL IS STUPID.
IT IS TIRESOME AND I FAIL
TO SEE THE PURPOSE.
EXPLAIN TO ME THE POINT BEHIND
RUNNING AROUND IN CIRCLES?
- AAH! WHY YOU--
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HIRAI, DO YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW SERIOUS IT IS
FOR A STUDENT TO KICK A TEACHER?
YOU'RE A PROBLEM STUDENT.
YOU'RE SUSPENDED.
NO, EXPELLED!
- WHAT A REPULSIVE TOAD.
- STOP LOOKING AT ME LIKE THAT.
- IS SHE ACTUALLY THINKING
OF HITTING HIM?
- Kondo:
WELL, SAY SOMETHING!
- HIRAI'S GONNA POP THE TEACHER.
LET'S HELP HER.
- RIGHT.
- THIS IS GONNA GET UGLY.
IT'S TOO LATE
TO STOP HER NOW.
- ARE YOU EVEN
LISTENING TO ME?!
- KICK HIM!
- ( grunting )
- Boy: DID YOU SEE--
- THANKS, SHANA.
- HMM.
- MR. KONDO, ARE YOU OKAY?
IT'S DANGEROUS JUST WANDERING
ONTO THE TRACK LIKE THAT.
RIGHT, EVERYONE?
- Ike: YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
- I SAW THE WHOLE THING.
- ME, TOO.
HIRAI'S A REALLY FAST RUNNER.
- A TRAFFIC ACCIDENT, MAN.
- Kondo: SAVAGES!
- SO YOU WANNA THREATEN HIM?
SHAKE HIM UP A LITTLE BIT?
- HMM.
I SEE YOU JUST HAPPEN TO BE
ON THE TRACK.
- Yuji: MR. KONDO, YOU SHOULD BE
A LITTLE MORE CAREFUL
IN THE FUTURE.
CAN WE GO NOW?
- Kondo: UH, FREE PERIOD, KIDS.
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- ( all cheering )
- WOW, SAKAI,
ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOU'RE BURSTING WITH CONFIDENCE.
- YOU WERE AWESOME, HIRAI.
- THAT FELT GREAT!
- ( all chattering )
- Yuji: THINGS WERE BEGINNING
TO LOOK UP, OR SO I THOUGHT.
WHAT I DIDN'T KNOW
WAS THAT SHANA WAS STARTING
TO FEEL A LITTLE UNEASY.
- I WAS GOING TO PUNCH HIM
IN THE FACE.
- KICK HIM!
- Alastor: I'M NOT TRYING
TO HEAP PRAISE UPON HIM,
BUT I THINK HE SHOWED
SUPERB JUDGMENT.
WITHOUT HIM, YOU WOULD HAVE
STRUCK THE TEACHER.
I BELIEVE THAT
WOULD HAVE RESULTED
IN SEVERE REPERCUSSIONS.
- HOW DARE HE?
GIVING ME ORDERS?
WHY?  WHY?
- WHAT IS IT ABOUT A MERE TORCH
THAT HAS YOU SO UPSET?
- THAT'S WHAT I'D LIKE TO KNOW.
- AH, THIS IS SO EXASPERATING.
I'M SENSING THE DENIZEN
AND THE FLAME HAZE,
BUT I CAN'T LOCK IN
ON THE CORPSE COLLECTOR.
- Marco: HE PROBABLY PLANNED IT
THAT WAY.
HE'S GOTCHA THIS TIME,
PARTNER. ( laughs )
- I'M GONNA GO IN
A LITTLE DEEPER.
- YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
WE'RE NOT THE FIRST TO ARRIVE.
IN A WAY
WE'RE TRESPASSING HERE.
- WHO CARES?
IF THEY WANNA COMPLAIN,
I'LL JUST HAVE TO KICK
THEIR TEETH DOWN THEIR THROAT.
- ( laughs )
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME!
I'M READY ANY TIME
YOU ARE!
- MATTHEW, MARK, LUKE
AND JOHN,
COVER ALL CORNERS AND FIND THE
GHOST WHO DISRUPTS OUR DREAMS.
- ( gasps )
- Alastor: IT APPEARS
THEY'RE STILL HERE,
EVEN THOUGH THEY MUST HAVE
SENSED OUR PRESENCE.
IT'S AN UNRESTRICTED METHOD USED
FOR SEARCHING A LARGE AREA.
ARE YOU SURE? THIS COULD END IN
A BATTLE IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL.
- AT LEAST I WON'T HAVE TO THINK
IF I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF A FIGHT.
- MARCO.
- Marco:
THEY'VE NOTICED US.
CANCEL YOUR SPELL.
THEY'RE READY TO FIGHT!
- THAT SUITS ME JUST FINE.
BE SEALED!
THERE THEY ARE.
- FLAMING HAIR!
- Marco:
BLAZING EYES!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING HERE?
- MY,
WHAT A RUDE LITTLE GIRL.
NOT EVEN A HELLO.
- ( Marco laughing )
LONG TIME NO SEE,
FLAME OF THE HEAVENS.
- ALASTOR,
DO YOU KNOW THESE TWO?
- MARCOSIAS, THE CLAWS
AND FANGS OF VIOLATION.
AND MARGERY DAW,
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
THEY'RE TOUGH
AND THEY WON'T BACK DOWN.
- IF YOU TWO JUST PACK UP
AND QUIETLY LEAVE THIS CITY,
I'LL GLADLY SEE YOU OFF.
- HUH.  WE WERE HERE FIRST.
I'M TAKING OUT
FRIAGNE MYSELF.
- Marco: SO THAT'S WHO IT IS!
IT'S THAT PERVERT
WITH THE DOLL FETISH.
- I'LL HAVE TO DEAL WITH HIM
LATER.
WE'VE COME HERE
FOR THE CORPSE COLLECTOR.
- Alastor: THE CORPSE COLLECTOR?
BUT HE'S AN EXCEPTION.
HE ACTUALLY GOES OUT OF HIS WAY
NOT TO UPSET THE BALANCE.
- EXCEPTION?
THERE ARE NO INNOCENTS
IN THE CRIMSON WORLD.
I PLAN ON KILLING
ALL OF THEM!
THE ONLY WAY TO DEAL WITH THEM
IS TO KILL, KILL, KILL!
- Marco: SHE'S WHAT YOU MIGHT
CALL A DEVOTED FLAME HAZE.
- Alastor:
YOUR HATRED FOR OTHERS
HAS BLINDED YOU TO THE TRUTH,
YOU BLOODTHIRSTY BASTARDS.
- Marco: PRETTY STRONG WORDS.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY, ALASTOR?
CAN WE FIGHT THEM NOW?
- WAIT.
- I TAKE IT YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO LEAVE.
- Marco: STRIKE THEM DOWN
WITHOUT MERCY,
MY BELOVED GOBLET,
MARGERY DAW.
THE REASON THIS PLACE
IS FILLED WITH TORCHES
IS BECAUSE THEY LEFT THAT
DENIZEN ALONE.
THEY'RE INCOMPETENT.
- INDEED. TOO BAD THEY WON'T
BE MORE OF A CHALLENGE.
GET READY FOR A SURPRISE.
- Alastor: WAIT.
DON'T BE RECKLESS.
- HMM.
- AAH!
HMM.  NOT BAD.
- Marco: SHE'S PRETTY SLICK.
- Alastor: THAT'S THE TOGA,
THE GOWN MADE OF FLAMES.
IT'S HER SPECIALTY.
BE CAUTIOUS.
- AAH!
- WHAT A LIVELY LITTLE BRAT.
- ( Marco laughing )
- YOU MISSED.
LET'S SEE
IF YOU CAN HIT ME NOW.
- Alastor:
BE CALM.  THINK FIRST.
- HYAH!
HYAH!
I DON'T HAVE TO THINK
OF ANYTHING.
I DON'T
BECAUSE I'M A FLAME HAZE!
THAT ONE.
- MISSED AGAIN.
- Marco: SURPRISE!
- HA!
- A FOX BRIDE'S
ELECTRICAL SHOWER.
- Marco: YOU'LL BE DEAD
WITHIN THE NEXT THREE SECONDS.
- AH.
- ARE YOU THE REAL
FLAME-HAIRED BLAZING-EYES?
- Marco: YOU'RE NOT AS STRONG
AS I THOUGHT YOU'D BE.
- ENOUGH OF THIS!
ONE FINAL ATTACK
AND THEN I'LL LET HER GO.
- Marco:
YEAH, THIS ISN'T ANY FUN.
GIVE HER A BIG BLAST
AND THEN LET'S CALL IT QUITS.
- THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
I MUST GET UP.
- THE PAIN OF A LIFE
OF HASTE AND STRIFE!
- GET UP.
- THAT WAS "SOLOMON GRUNDY."
- Alastor: WATCH OUT!
MOVE!
- THERE!
GAME OVER.
- AAH!
- ( choir chanting )
- WHY?
WHY?!
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: TWO GIRLS
STRUGGLE WITH INNER TURMOIL.
SHANA'S STILL CONFUSED
WHILE KAZUMI DEALS
WITH HER FEELINGS
FOR SOMEONE ELSE.
MEANWHILE, THE HUNTER AND THE
CHANTER OF ELEGIES CLASH.
NEXT EPISODE...