- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE CRIMSON
WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Boy:
IT HAPPENED IN MISAKI CITY,
WHEN THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS
WERE IN FULL BLOOM.
THEY WERE LATER
THAN USUAL THIS YEAR.
MY NAME IS YUJI SAKAI.
THE SCHOOL YEAR HAD JUST BEGUN,
AND I WAS SETTLING
INTO THE DAILY ROUTINE
THAT WAS THE LIFE
OF A HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT.
A MORNING NO DIFFERENT
FROM ANY OTHER.
NOTHING OUT OF THE ORDINARY.
DAYS LIKE THAT WERE SUPPOSED
TO LAST FOREVER.
- ( wind howls )
- OOH!
Yuji: AT THE TIME,
I COULDN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO IMAGINE WHAT
WAS ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
I HAD NO INKLING
OF THIS STRANGE,
DIVERGENT WORLD I WAS SOON
TO ENCOUNTER
OR OF THE FACT
THAT I WAS ABOUT TO DIE.
- ( crashing )
- ( snarling )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
AAH!
- IT'S YUM-YUM TIME.
( shrieking )
- AND THEN, I SAW HER.
THE GIRL WITH THE FLAME RED
HAIR AND BLAZING EYES.
( gasping )
Yuji:
THAT WAS THE DAY MY WORLD
CHANGED FOREVER.
Yuji: THE DAY BEGAN WHEN
I MET UP WITH HAYATO IKE,
A BUDDY FROM JUNIOR HIGH.
MY LAST MORNING
WAS JUST SO NORMAL.
- HEY, SAKAI!
( panting )
- HMM?  HI.
IT DOESN'T EVEN FEEL LIKE
I'VE MOVED UP TO HIGH
SCHOOL WITH YOU HERE.
YOU KNOW,
NOTHING'S CHANGED, REALLY.
- HEY, DON'T MAKE IT MY FAULT.
I MEAN, YOU'RE SMART ENOUGH.
YOU COULD'VE GONE ANYWHERE.
- YEAH, BUT I'D RATHER STICK
CLOSE TO HOME.
- IT'S A BIT UNFAIR YOU GOT
TO CHOOSE THIS SCHOOL
FOR THAT REASON.
I MEAN, MY MARKS WERE
BARELY GOOD ENOUGH
TO GET ME IN THE DOOR.
- YOU SAY THAT,
BUT YOU'RE THE KIND OF PERSON
WHO ALWAYS FINDS SOME WAY
TO GET WHAT HE WANTS.
- MAYBE I'M JUST LUCKY.
- MAYBE YOU'RE JUST SHREWD.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
MY HEAD WAS FILLED
WITH THOUGHTS OF HIGH SCHOOL
AND WHAT IT WAS GONNA BE LIKE.
HUH?
- YO!
- OH, UH, GOOD MORNING!
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO YELL.
- WHOA, HE'S JUST
A LITTLE STANDOFFISH.
- THAT'S SATO. I HEAR HE WAS
A REAL TROUBLEMAKER
IN JUNIOR HIGH.
BUT YOU SEE THAT JOCK
NEXT TO HIM?
I THINK HIS NAME IS TANAKA.
ANYWAY, SATO'S REALLY
CALMED DOWN A LOT
SINCE THEY
STARTED HANGING OUT.
- REALLY?
- I'VE MET GUYS
LIKE THAT BEFORE.
THEY THINK WE'RE JUST A COUPLE
OF BORING HONOR STUDENTS,
NOT EVEN WORTH TALKING TO.
- WE'RE HONOR STUDENTS?
YEAH, WELL, MAYBE YOU ARE,
BUT I'M SURE NOT.
- WELL, IT'S NOT UNUSUAL TO HAVE
ONE OR TWO GUYS IN A CLASS
WHO JUST DON'T FIT IN,
SO THERE'S NO USE
WORRYING ABOUT IT.
- YEAH.
SCHOOL HAD STARTED A WEEK AGO.
THOUGH IT WASN'T
A NON-STOP PARTY,
AT LEAST IT WASN'T A BOTTOMLESS
PIT OF DESPAIR, EITHER.
I HAD A NORMAL LIFE, AND THINGS
WERE STARTING TO LOOK PROMISING.
THANKS.
THERE WERE SOME PRETTY CUTE
GIRLS IN THOSE CLASSES.
FROM A MALE POINT-OF-VIEW,
THINGS WERE DEFINITELY
LOOKING UP.
- Teacher: SAKAI?
- HUH?
- YUJI SAKAI, RIGHT?
- YES, YES, I AM.
- WELL, WHAT WERE YOU STARING
OFF INTO SPACE FOR?
READ THE NEXT PART.
- I, UH--
- Boy: BUSTED!
- ( class murmuring )
- Boy: WATCH THIS!
"MY FATHER HAD JUST RETURNED
FROM TOKYO.
I WAS TO START ATTENDING
THE SCHOOL BUILT
WHERE THE FAMILY STUDY CENTER
ONCE STOOD.
AND I WOULD HAVE TO MAKE
THE LONG WALK EVERY DAY.
TO GET TO THE SCHOOL FROM HOME,
I HAD TO PASS THROUGH A WICKET
THAT WAS BUILT
INTO OUR WEST GATE.
THERE'S STILL THE REMAINS OF
A GUARD HOUSE NEAR THE WICKET.
A MAN IN HIS 50s LIVES THERE
WITH HIS WIFE AND CHILD."
WELL, THINGS WENT ON AS USUAL,
BUT I'M NOT COMPLAINING.
I HAD NO IDEA MY LIFE
WAS SO FRAGILE.
ALL IT TOOK WAS FIVE MINUTES
FOR IT TO COLLAPSE
AND COME UNDONE.
- ( maniacal laughing )
- Yuji: GOT ANY PLANS?
- Ike: SAMPLE EXAM
AT MY PREP SCHOOL.
- PREP SCHOOL?  YOU'RE PREPARING
FOR UNIVERSITY ALREADY?
- WELL, I GOTTA MAKE
MY PARENTS HAPPY.
SEE, MY ALLOWANCE DEPENDS
ON IT.  AND YOU?
- HMM.
I'VE GOT SOME FREE TIME.
I THINK I'LL CHECK OUT THE CDs
BY THE TRAIN STATION.
- SEE YA.
- Yuji:
THINKING BACK, I WONDER
HOW THINGS WOULD HAVE TURNED OUT
IF I'D GONE STRAIGHT HOME.
WOULD MY FATE HAVE BEEN THE SAME
IF I'D BEEN SOMEPLACE ELSE?
BUT I HAD NO IDEA
AT THE TIME
THAT I WAS ONLY A FEW METERS
AWAY FROM THE SPOT
WHERE THE WORLD WAS
GOING TO BE DISPLACED.
- ( grunting )
- HUH?
- OH.
- HI.  I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
LIVED OUT THIS WAY, SAKAI.
- NO, I JUST CAME IN HERE
TO LOOK AT THE CDs.
I LIVE IN OGAWA CHO.
- WOW, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I LIVE IN AIZAWA CHO.
JUST AFTER SHIN MISAKIDORI.
- WOW, THAT'S REALLY CLOSE.
- YEP.
- OH, BY THE WAY, THANKS FOR
THE HELP IN LANGUAGE CLASS.
- WELL, SOMETIMES I DON'T
PAY ATTENTION, EITHER.
- COVER FOR ME NEXT TIME.
- YOU GOT IT.
- I COULDN'T HELP NOTICING,
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE IKE'S
WITH YOU TODAY.
- NO, HE COULDN'T MAKE IT,
'CAUSE HE'S GOT PREP SCHOOL.
WHAT'S UP?
- NOTHING.
IT'S JUST YOU'RE
ALWAYS TOGETHER.
- WE'RE NOT ALWAYS TOGETHER.
- HEY, SAKAI.
I WAS SORT OF WONDERING.
DO YOU KNOW IF IKE HAS
A GIRLFRIEND OR ANYTHING?
- NO, NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
- HMM.  I SEE.
- WELL, I THINK I'M GONNA DROP
BY THE STATION BUILDING.
- OKAY, TAKE IT EASY.
- I GET IT.
SHE LIKES IKE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HOW
HE REACTS TO THIS.
- ( distant shrieking )
HMM?
- ( laughing )
- COME BACK HERE, YOU SCAMP.
- HEY, KID, WATCH OUT!
THIS CAN'T BE.
WHAT THE-- WHAT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
( gasps )
- OKAY, I'M READY.
- THERE AREN'T AS MANY
AS I FIRST THOUGHT.
BUT THERE SHOULD BE MORE THAN
ENOUGH.  LET THE FEAST BEGIN.
- YEAH, LET'S EAT!
LET'S EAT!
( gasps )
- SO YUMMY.
TASTE SO YUMMY!
- YOU MUSTN'T TALK WHILE YOU'RE
EATING.  IT'S BAD MANNERS.
- SORRY.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
HIRAI!
- HELLO.
- WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
HE DOESN'T SEEM TO BE A DENIZEN.
- AND HE'S MOVING AROUND INSIDE
THE SEALED ZONE.
- AH, HE'S A MYSTES!
- WHAT?  A MYSTES?
ONE OF THOSE TORCHES
WITH TREASURE IN IT?
- YES, AND A RARE SPECIMEN
AT THAT.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE SINCE
WE'VE FOUND SUCH A GIFT.
THE MASTER WILL BE PLEASED.
- OH, BOY!
COMING HERE WAS A GREAT IDEA.
- AAH!
- I GOTCHA! ( laughs )
IT'S YUM-YUM TIME.
( shrieks )
- WHO DID THAT?
- WHO-- WHO IS THIS GIRL?
- SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK,
ALASTOR?
- HMM, THEY'RE NOT ALLIES.
THEY'RE ONLY RINNE.
- ( Rinne shrieks )
YOU CUT MY ARM OFF!
- ( gasps )
- I'LL CRUSH YOU.
- ( screams )
WHAT?  WHO-- WHO--
WHO IS SHE?
OH, NO!
NOW PUPI KNOW YOU.
( screaming )
DON'T DO IT!
- ALL I DID WAS DESTROY
ITS SHELL.
- ITS REAL BODY ESCAPED
AT THE LAST MINUTE.
- IT COULD STILL BE CLOSE BY.
- IS THIS A MYSTES?
- A SOMEWHAT UNUSUAL ONE,
I SEE.
- ( gasps ) A WHAT?
( gasps )
- ( grunts )
( screams )
- SO THERE WAS SOMETHING INSIDE
THAT MYSTES
THAT YOU REALLY WANTED.
- FLAMING HAIR, BLAZING EYES.
YOU'RE ALASTOR'S FLAME HAZE,
HE WHO IS THE FLAME OF HEAVEN.
JUST A TOOL FOR DESTRUCTION.
- THAT'S RIGHT, AND SO WHAT?
- MY MASTER WILL NOT BE PLEASED
WHEN HE HEARS OF THIS.
- TOO BAD.  HE'LL BE SCREAMING
IN HIS LAST MOMENTS BEFORE LONG.
- DAMN YOU!
- BUT THIS IS NOW.
YOU CAN DO
THE SCREAMING INSTEAD.
- NO!  WAIT A MINUTE.
- HMM.
- HUH?
( gasps )
( panting ) WHAT--
WHAT'S-- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
IT'S INSIDE ME
REACHING FOR SOMETHING.
STOP IT.
- ( screams )
- I'VE BEEN CUT.
I'VE BEEN CUT!
- SO THAT'S ITS TRUE FORM.
- BEHIND YOU.
- ( shrieking )
- IT'S ESCAPED FOR NOW,
BUT FROM WHAT IT SAID,
THERE SEEMS TO BE A POWERFUL
ENTITY SOMEWHERE IN THE SHADOWS.
- WE MAY BE ABLE TO SEAL THE
KING OF THE CRIMSON WORLD AGAIN.
- IN ANY CASE.
- HELP ME.
- I WAS TAKEN BY SURPRISE.
I'D FORGOTTEN THAT THING
WAS STILL MOVING AROUND.
- INDEED, FOR A MOMENT THERE,
I WAS REMINDED
OF TENMOKU IKKO.
- YES, BUT WE KNEW FROM
THE VERY BEGINNING THAT
THAT ONE COULD MOVE
AND FIGHT FREELY.
- PLEASE.
I NEED AN AMBULANCE.
- SO NOISY.  JUST SHUT UP.
SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
IT'S USELESS
CRYING OVER A CUT NOW.
- IT DIDN'T HAVE MUCH EXISTENCE
WHEN IT WAS ALIVE.
IF IT WAS HUMAN,
IT WOULD HAVE DIED THE MOMENT
IT RECEIVED A CUT THAT DEEP.
- IF I WAS HUMAN?
I HAVE TO STOP
THE BLEEDING BEFORE--
THE BLEEDING?
WHERE'S THE BLOOD?
THERE'S NO PAIN.
- ( scoffs )
- ( gasps )
( shouts )
I'M ON FIRE!  HUH?
BUT I JUST--
- NOW LET'S SEE...
- HUH?  OH, NO!  HIRAI!
GOOD.  SHE'S OKAY.
MAN, WHAT A RELIEF.
- I STILL HAVE TO
FIX THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
BUT THAT SHOULD DO IT
FOR THE TORCHES.
- HMM, THEY WERE CONSUMING THEM
WITHOUT RESTRAINT.
- IT LOOKS LIKE THEIR MASTER
HAS QUITE THE APPETITE.
I'M DONE.
- EVERYONE'S STILL WALKING
AROUND LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED.
HUH?  HIRAI!
HIRAI!  WAIT FOR ME!
( gasps )
WHAT?  WHAT IS THAT?
HIRAI.  HUH?
THAT KID.  BUT WHY?
DOES THIS MEAN--
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED BACK THERE?
WHERE DID THAT GIRL
FROM BEFORE DISAPPEAR TO?
AND THOSE FLAMES ON EVERYONE--
- HEY, STOP BUGGIN' ME,
ALL RIGHT?
MAYBE WE SHOULD GET RID
OF THIS ONE, ALASTOR.
- BUT WHAT ARE YOU--
- NO, WE MUSTN'T OPEN
A MYSTES CARELESSLY.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN ALL
THE TROUBLE TENMOKU IKKO CAUSED?
- I REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT IT KEEPS BUGGING ME.
- JUST TELL IT THE TRUTH.
IT'S THE BEST WAY
TO SHUT IT UP.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU KEEP CALLING ME "IT"
LIKE I'M SOME THING.
- YES, THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU ARE A THING.
- YOU'RE NOT HUMAN.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S NOT ONLY YOU.
EVERYONE WALKING AROUND
WITH A FLAME
IN THEIR BODY IS A THING.
THEY ARE REPLACEMENTS OF PEOPLE
WHO HAD THEIR EXISTENCE CONSUMED
BY DENIZENS
OF THE CRIMSON WORLD.
THEY'RE TORCHES.
- THEY'RE REPLACEMENTS?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THIS WORLD'S BALANCE
WOULD BE DISRUPTED
IF THEY DISAPPEARED
TOO SUDDENLY.
THEREFORE, REPLACEMENTS
FOR THOSE PEOPLE ARE PROVIDED
TO SOFTEN THE IMPACT.
THEY'RE TEMPORARY.
- BUT THEN
YOU'RE SAYING WE'RE--
- I'M VERY SORRY, MASTER.
I LOST ONE
OF YOUR PRECIOUS RINNE.
- YOU'VE NOTHING TO
BE SORRY FOR, MARIANNE.
BEING ATTACKED BY A FLAME HAZE
CAN BE LIKENED
TO ENCOUNTERING
A NATURAL DISASTER.
- PLEASE,
GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE.
- I SHALL,
BUT THERE'S NO NEED TO HURRY.
YOU MUST BE TIRED.
GET SOME REST FIRST.
GOOD NIGHT,
MY OH-SO-ADORABLE MARIANNE.
YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
( kisses )
HAIR AFLAME, EYES ABLAZE.
- Yuji: I'M NOT ALIVE?
- NO.
THE REAL YOU HAS HAD
ITS EXISTENCE CONSUMED
AND IS NO LONGER LIVING.
RIGHT NOW,
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT RESIDUE.
- ( gasping )
I-- I DON'T EXIST ANYMORE.
Yuji: THAT DAY
THAT STARTED
JUST LIKE ANY OTHER DAY,
THE DAY THAT I FOUND OUT
I WAS DEAD.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji:
I AM ALREADY DEAD.
AND EVEN AS I TRY TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT THAT REALLY MEANS,
A YOUNG GIRL FINDS HERSELF
ON THE VERGE
OF DISAPPEARING AS WELL.
NEXT EPISODE--
"THE LIT FLAME."