Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
Yuji: THERE ARE MANY
TYPES OF ENCOUNTERS.
SOME OF THEM CAN LEAD TO
CONFRONTATION OR EVEN BATTLE.
- THOSE THREE ARE DENIZENS!
- SHOULD WE REALLY
BE LETTIN' EM GO?
- Marco: WE DIDN'T LET THEM GO.
THEY LET US GO.
- Margery: SHUT UP,
STUPID MARCO.
( phone ringing )
- Yuji: WHILE OTHER
ENCOUNTERS MIGHT CONSIST
OF A SIMPLE CONVERSATION
BETWEEN A LORD FROM ANOTHER
REALM AND A HOUSEWIFE.
- BESIDES, GIRLS CAN BE
QUITE PRECOCIOUS.
THEY'RE MORE MATURE
THAN THEY APPEAR.
- Alastor: MADAME.
- Yuji: AND WHAT ABOUT
SHANA AND I?
WHERE'S THAT GOING?
I HAD THE FEELING I WOULDN'T
KNOW THE ANSWER
TO THAT ANY TIME SOON.
- HUH?
- HUH.
- WHOA.
- I'LL NEVER DO IT WITH YOU.
- Ike: DON'T LOOK SO WORRIED.
HIRAI AND SAKAI ARE
JUST GOOD FRIENDS,
THEY'RE NOT IN LOVE
WITH EACH OTHER.
- Yoshida: HMM, I CAN'T HELP IT!
I AM WORRIED.
I HAVE FEELINGS FOR HIM.
AND I THINK MAYBE YUKARI
CARES FOR HIM TOO.
BUT THEN, WHO DOES SAKAI LIKE?
( groans )
I'VE GOTTA STOP
THINKING ABOUT IT.
( cat meows )
HUH?
IT'S A LITTLE EARLY, BUT LET'S
GO FOR A WALK, EKATERINA.
( panting )
- Yuji: SHANA!
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
GO A LITTLE SLOWER?
WE JUST FINISHED TRAINING.
THIS IS A BIT MUCH.
- SHUT UP AND RUN!
- ( sighs ) I ONLY CAME BECAUSE
YOU SAID YOU HAD SOMETHING
TO SHOW ME.
OH WELL, IT BETTER BE WORTH IT!
NOW THAT'S...
A VIEW.
- I LOVE THE WAY IT
LOOKS AT NIGHT.
- ( meows )
- DON'T RUN OFF LIKE THAT!
- ( sighs )
- HOW COULD SAKAI BE
SO CASUAL ABOUT THIS?
I DON'T GET IT. DOESN'T HE KNOW
HOW YOSHIDA FEELS ABOUT HIM?
I MEAN, SHE'S LOYAL, SHE'S
ATTENTIVE, SHE'S ADMIRABLE.
SO WHAT'S NOT TO LIKE ABOUT HER?
SHE'S JUST GREAT!
- ( gasps )
- Ike: MORNING!
- OH, GOOD MORNING IKE.
YOU'RE EARLY TODAY.
- YOU OKAY?
- I, I WOKE UP REALLY
EARLY THIS MORNING.
I DIDN'T GET MUCH SLEEP.
I WALKED MY DOG DOWN TO THE
RIVERBANK. AND THEN I...
AND THEN I...
- Sorath: ( laughing )
WHAT A FEAST!
- YOU SURE YOU WANT ME
TO HOLD ON TO THE ORGEL?
- YES. I'M UNEASY LETTING
MY BROTHER TAKE CARE OF IT.
WE HAVE TO FIND THE OWNER
OF THE NIETONO NO SHANA
AND MAKE THEM
HAND IT OVER TO US.
- Sydonay: SHE DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING YESTERDAY,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
IS GOING TO LEAVE US
ALONE FOR MUCH LONGER.
EVEN YOU TWO WOULD HAVE
TROUBLE TAKING ON
TWO FLAME HAZES
AT THE SAME TIME.
- I'M NOT WORRIED,
AND I'M THE ONE MAKING
THE DECISIONS,
SO JUST FOLLOW
INSTRUCTIONS.
YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO
THAT FLAME HAZES
DON'T LIKE TO TEAM UP.
IF ANY OTHER
INSIGNIFICANTS ATTACK,
THEN I'LL FINISH THEM OFF AS
WELL. IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
- HMM, I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
BUT TAKING HER LIGHTLY
COULD BE VERY DANGEROUS.
- OH DON'T WORRY.
AS LONG AS WE STAY INSIDE THIS
CRADLE GARDEN, WE'RE INVINCIBLE.
THAT'S WHY IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT YOU TAKE CARE OF THE ORGEL.
THAT'S NOT TOO HARD
TO UNDERSTAND, IS IT?
- Tanaka: PLEASE BIG SISTER,
TELL US WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
- HUH?
- IT'S NOT TRUE THAT
THE DENIZENS LET US GO, IS IT?
THE TRUTH IS YOU
COULDN'T FIGHT THEM,
BECAUSE YOU WERE WORRIED
ABOUT OUR SAFETY, RIGHT?
IT BURNS ME UP THAT
YOU WERE HUMILIATED LIKE THAT,
BECAUSE WE WERE
HOLDING YOU BACK.
PLEASE, SAY SOMETHING!
BIG SISTER!
- HAVING LUNCH ON THE ROOF
IS KIND OF A NICE CHANGE.
- Yuji: I GUESS.
- I WANNA TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED EARLY
THIS MORNING.
I HAD TROUBLE SLEEPING,
SO I WENT FOR A STROLL DOWN
BY THE MANA RIVER.
I SAW YOU DOWN BY THE RIVERBANK.
- OH?
- IKE.
- YOU SAID NOTHING'S GOING ON.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
YOU ACCEPT YOSHIDA'S AFFECTIONS,
BUT THEN YOU GO AND DO THAT?
- Yuji: WELL, THAT'S...
- Ike: DO YOU THINK
THAT'S RIGHT?
- HMM?
- I SAID, "DO YOU
THINK THAT'S RIGHT?"
IF YOU KEEP PLAYING
GAMES LIKE THIS,
YOU'RE GONNA END UP
HURTING SOMEONE.
- Yoshida: STOP IT!
I NEVER ASKED YOU
TO DO THIS, IKE.
- I DIDN'T ASK FOR THIS.
- BUT YOSHIDA.
- I'M NOT LIKE THAT. I'M NOT!
- ( door slams )
- Ike: ACTUALLY, YOSHIDA
WAS THE ONE
WHO SAW YOU TWO
THIS MORNING, NOT ME.
- Yuji: I SEE.
- Ike: SHE TOLD ME
ABOUT IT BEFORE CLASS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
I REACTED THAT WAY,
BUT WHEN I SAW YOU EATING
THE LUNCH SHE'D MADE FOR YOU,
I JUST COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
I GUESS I STUCK MY NOSE IN
WHERE I SHOULDN'T HAVE.
I DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING BY IT.
- I GUESS YOU SCREW UP
EVERY NOW AND THEN, TOO.
- SCREW UP?
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT. SORRY.
- IT'S COOL.
I'M EMBARRASSED TO ADMIT IT,
BUT THERE'S AN ELEMENT OF TRUTH
TO WHAT YOU SAID.
BUT MAYBE YOU SHOULD'VE
JUST KEPT IT BETWEEN US.
- YEAH.
- Yuji: HEY, CAN I ASK
YOU A QUESTION?
- SURE.
- DO YOU HAVE
FEELINGS FOR YOSHIDA?
- ( Yoshida crying )
- I'M SO STUPID.
I'M JUST SUCH AN IDIOT.
IKE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG,
BUT I PANICKED,
JUST BECAUSE HE HAD THE COURAGE
TO SAY THE THINGS I COULDN'T.
I'M SO AFRAID TO SAY ANYTHING.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD WORK OUT
IF I LEFT THINGS ALONE.
JUST BECAUSE THEY'RE ALWAYS
HANGING AROUND EACH OTHER,
IT DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
AND THEY LOOK SO
NATURAL TOGETHER.
I THOUGHT IF I TRIED
TO COME BETWEEN THEM,
WHATEVER CONNECTION
I HAD WITH SAKAI,
HOWEVER SMALL IT MIGHT BE,
WOULD BE BROKEN.
AND I'D BE LEFT ALONE.
- WHY DID YOU RUN AWAY?
- RUN AWAY?
YOU'RE NOT BEING FAIR, YUKARI!
- FAIR ABOUT WHAT?
- YOU MUST HAVE FEELINGS FOR HIM
TOO. ADMIT IT, YOU LIKE HIM!
- ( gasps )
- ME? HAVE FEELINGS FOR YUJI?
- Yoshida:
YOU'RE ALWAYS SO COLD,
AND YOU ACT LIKE YOU DON'T CARE.
BUT YOU'RE SO MUCH
CLOSER TO HIM THAN I AM.
- IT'S NOT FAIR!
- Shana: IT DOESN'T CONCERN YOU.
- YOU'RE RUNNING AWAY TOO.
RUNNING FROM THE TRUTH.
- I'M WHAT?
WHY SHOULD I STAND HERE
AND TAKE THIS
KIND OF TALK FROM YOU?
- I HAVE THE RIGHT
TO SAY IT.
'CAUSE I LOVE HIM TOO.
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I JUST SAID?
I LOVE SAKAI!
- YUJI. YUJI IS MY...
HE'S MY...
WHAT IS HE?
- MAYBE YOU'RE
RIGHT, YUKARI.
MAYBE I WAS RUNNING AWAY,
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
I'VE DECIDED I'M
NOT GONNA RELY ON OTHERS
AND LEAVE THINGS UNSAID.
I CAN DO A LOT OF THINGS,
AND I'M GONNA DO
THE BEST I CAN, MY WAY.
YUKARI HAVE YOU EVER TOLD SAKAI
THAT YOU HAVE FEELINGS FOR HIM?
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
I TELL HIM MY FEELINGS.
- YOU CAN'T
- AND I'M GONNA TELL HIM MYSELF.
- NO, DON'T!
- AND I'M GONNA TELL HIM
THAT I LOVE HIM.
- NO, YOU CAN'T!
YOU CAN NEVER TELL HIM THAT!
- I WILL! I'LL TELL HIM!
WE'LL LET SAKAI CHOOSE.
I'M NOT GONNA LOSE. YOU HAVEN'T
EVEN TOLD HIM HOW YOU FEEL.
- YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
I ALSO HAVE FEELINGS.
I ALSO HAVE FEELINGS FOR HIM!
- HUH? I THINK THIS IS A...
IT'S A SEAL.
- WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
WHO ARE YOU TO STAND IN MY WAY?
WHEN I'M DONE, I'M GONNA COME
BACK AND TELL YOU HOW I FEEL.
YOU DON'T STAND
A CHANCE WITH HIM.
YUJI AND I HAVE A LOT
GOING ON BETWEEN US.
YOU ARE CRAZY IF YOU THINK
THAT I'M GONNA LOSE TO YOU.
( echoing ) I WILL NOT
LOSE TO YOU!
- Sorath: HEY TIRIEL!
I CAN SENSE IT.
THE NIETONO NO SHANA
IS OVER THERE!
- Tiriel: VERY WELL THEN.
LET US RETRIEVE IT TOGETHER,
WITHOUT FURTHER DELAY,
DEAR BROTHER.
- ( explosion )
- ENGULFED IN LOVE,
THE SIBLINGS FROM YESTERDAY.
THEY'RE COOKING UP
SOMETHING BIG OUT THERE.
- Marco: WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO, MARGERY DAW,
MY BEAUTIFUL GOBLET?
LET THEM LET US ESCAPE AGAIN?
- YEAH, AFTER ALL,
THEY'RE NOT AFTER ME.
THERE'S NO REASON TO GO THROUGH
THE TROUBLE OF A CONFRONTATION.
- WHY NOT? WHY DON'T
YOU WANNA GO?
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
TO BE THIS TIMID.
WE'LL DO EVERYTHING WE CAN
NOT TO GET IN YOUR WAY.
PLEASE, BIG SISTER, FIGHT THEM!
- Sato: NEVER MIND.
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA GO,
THEN I'LL HEAD OVER THERE.
I'D RATHER DO THAT THAN BE SEEN
AS SOMEONE WHO HOLDS YOU BACK.
- Margery: LISTEN YOU TWO...
- Tanaka: I'M GOING WITH HIM,
BIG SISTER.
I'LL SHOW YOU THAT WHEN
I HAVE TO, I CAN FIGHT TOO.
- Margery: ALRIGHT,
ALRIGHT ALREADY.
WE'LL START BY HEADING OVER
TO THE DEPARTMENT STORE.
THAT PRESENT THE DOLL FREAK LEFT
FOR US MIGHT COME IN HANDY.
- LET'S DO IT!
- Yuji: IS THIS A SEAL?
- Shana: LOOKS LIKE IT,
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY IT'S SO BIG.
- COULD IT BE A TRAP
OF SOME SORT?
- I SENSE THREE DENZIENS.
TWO OF THEM ARE COMING THIS WAY.
- Alastor: AND ONE IS
STAYING PUT.
- THREE AGAINST ONE,
NOT THE BEST ODDS.
- HEY SHANA, MARGERY, HOW 'BOUT
IF WE ASK HER TO HELP OUT?
- REMEMBER WHEN WE
SAW HER BY THE POOL?
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
WON'T BE OF ANY USE TO US NOW.
- Alastor: OUR FIRST PRIORITY
IS TO DEAL WITH THE ONES
COMING AFTER US.
- Mmm.
- Hmm.
- YUJI, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO GO AND HIDE SOMEWHERE.
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE,
I'M GOING WITH YOU!
- THIS BATTLE COULD
BE DANGEROUS.
- I'M READY.
- IF THESE DENIZENS ATTACK
YOU WITH SOMETHING YOUR
FIRE REPELLING
RING CAN'T HANDLE,
YOU'LL BE WIPED OUT INSTANTLY.
- Alastor: THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO IN THIS BATTLE.
THEREFORE, THERE'S NO REASON
FOR YOU TO COME WITH US.
- OKAY THEN.
- HOWEVER, THERE IS ONE
THING THAT PUZZLES ME.
- Alastor: MAINTAINING A
SEAL OF THIS SIZE
REQUIRES AN ENORMOUS AMOUNT
OF THE POWER OF EXISTENCE.
MORE THAN IS AVAILABLE HERE.
DO YOU SEE WHAT I'M GETTING AT?
- I THINK SO. YOU'RE SAYING
THERE'S SOME KIND OF DEVICE
OR SOMETHING
HOLDING THIS SEAL UP.
- YES. A TREASURE,
AN UNRESTRICTED METHOD,
OR EVEN SOMETHING
WE'VE NEVER HEARD ABOUT.
- OKAY THEN, I'LL HEAD OUT
AND LOOK FOR IT!
- Alastor: JUST CALM DOWN.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
THAT EASY TO FIND.
- DON'T FORGET, OUR OPPONENTS
HAVE CONTROL OVER
THE ENTIRE CITY.
YOU COULD BE ATTACKED
BY A RINNE,
OR EVEN A DENIZEN,
WITHOUT WARNING.
- DENIZENS AND RINNE. RIGHT.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN TO HELP.
- THANKS.
- HEY SHANA,
IF I END UP HELPING YOU,
HOW 'BOUT YOU GIVE ME
A LITTLE REWARD?
- A REWARD?
JUST SHUT UP! SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
- GET OUTTA HERE!
- RIGHT. SEE YA!
- Alastor: LET'S GO.
- Sorath: LOOK, LOOK TIRIEL!
IT'S THE NIETONO NO SHANA!
THE NIETONO NO
SHANA'S RIGHT THERE!
- ( laughs )
- Tiriel: INDEED IT IS,
DEAR BROTHER.
PLEASE, WAIT JUST
A LITTLE LONGER.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
THIS IS ENGULFED IN SELF-LOVE,
AND I'M ENGULFED IN
LOVE FOR OTHERS.
WE'RE ALSO KNOWN
AS SORATH AND TIRIEL.
FORGIVE MY ASKING, BUT
WHO ARE YOU IN A CONTRACT WITH?
- I AM THE FLAME HAZE OF
ALASTOR, THE FLAME OF HEAVEN.
I AM THE FLAME-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER, SHANA!
- THE FLAME OF HEAVEN
IS AN OLD NAME
IF I'M NOT VERY MUCH MISTAKEN,
BUT NONE OF THAT
REALLY MATTERS RIGHT NOW.
WE ONLY MADE THIS
LITTLE SIDE TRIP
TO HAVE A BRIEF
MOMENT OF FUN WITH YOU.
- SIDE TRIP?
WHO ARE THESE TWO?
UGH, IT'S CREEPY THE WAY THEY'RE
HANGING ON TO EACH OTHER.
- THE REASON WE'RE
HERE IS SIMPLE,
I WANT YOU TO GIVE THAT
SWORD YOU'RE HOLDING
TO MY BROTHER, SORATH.
- YOU WANT ME TO WHAT?
- IS THERE SOMETHING
WRONG WITH YOUR EARS?
OR MAYBE IT'S YOUR BRAIN.
- I SAID I WANT YOU
TO GIVE THAT SWORD...
- I HEARD YOU!
- I WANT THE NIETONO NO SHANA!
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs ) SO, TELL ME,
HOW DO YOU LIKE THE TASTE OF
MY BROTHER'S BLOOD SUCKER?
WHEN YOU ADD
POWER OF EXISTENCE TO IT,
YOU CAN INJURE
YOUR OPPONENT BY MERELY
TOUCHING THE
OTHER PERSON'S SWORD.
- THAT IS NOT GOOD.
- Alastor: WE CAN'T
ATTACK RECKLESSLY.
- I WANT THE NIETONO
NO SHANA REAL BAD!
WAIT! COME BACK,
NIETONO NO SHANA!
- Tanaka: SO, EVERYONE'S
FROZEN BECAUSE OF
AN UNRESTRICTED METHOD?
- Marco: YEAH, YOU GOTTA HAND IT
TO THOSE PERVERTED SIBLINGS,
THEY THREW THIS WHOLE THING UP,
AND WE DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE.
- Sato: UH, WHAT'S THE
SITUATION NOW?
- OUT OF THE THREE
WE RAN INTO YESTERDAY,
TWO OF THEM ARE
FIGHTING THE LITTLE BRAT.
THE OTHER ONE IS
SOMEWHERE OUTSIDE THE CITY.
- SO WHEN ARE YOU GOING?
- WHY SHOULD I GO?
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU ALREADY,
IT'S NOT AS IF THEY'RE AFTER ME.
HMM...
- Sato: MISS MARGERY?
- NOW WHAT?
- ONE OF THE TORCHES IS MOVING.
- Marco: WHAT?
- ARE YOU SURE?
- OH MAN, WHY DID I SAY
I WANTED TO HELP OUT?
THIS IS CREEPY.
I'D BE SAFE IF
I JUST STAYED HERE.
NO, I CAN'T DO THAT.
IF I WANNA HELP THEM,
I HAVE TO GO OUT.
I HOPE NOTHING'S OUT THERE.
- ( gasping )
- I'M OKAY.
- Alastor: WE UNDERESTIMATED
THEIR ABILITIES.
- GIVE ME THE NIETONO NO SHANA.
- YOU CAN FORGET IT!
- ( screams )
- ( laughs )
- AH, WHAT A PLEASANT SIGHT.
- ( panting )
- OKAY. HUH? A DENIZEN? RINNE?
- NOW GO, BROTHER,
TAKE IT FROM HER HANDS.
- THE NIETONO NO SHANA,
IT'S MINE!
AT LAST IT'S MINE!
MINE ALL MINE!
- NOW!
- ( yelling )
- HUH?
- ( screams )
- AH! SORATH, NO!
- YOU'RE NEXT.
- THAT WAS AWESOME!
SO THAT'S THE
NIETONO NO SHANA'S POWER!
YOU'VE GOT A FLAME SWORD!
- ( laughs )
- Alastor: THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HE RECOVERED TOO QUICKLY.
- NOW I GET IT, ALASTOR.
THIS MONSTER'S SEAL IS
DIFFERENT FROM THE OTHERS.
IT'S MORE LIKE A FACTORY
DESIGNED TO SUPPLY THEM WITH AN
UNINTERRUPTED POWER
OF EXISTENCE.
- Alastor: HMM,
THAT MAKES SENSE.
IT WOULD
EXPLAIN THEIR GREAT
POWER AND THAT RECOVERY
WE JUST WITNESSED.
- QUESTION IS, WHERE ARE
THESE TWO HIDING
THE REAL SOURCE OF THEIR POWER.
- IT'S UNFORGIVABLE.
TO THINK SOMEONE LIKE YOU
ACTUALLY HURT MY BROTHER,
AND THEN THE MOST
HORRENDOUS INSULT OF ALL,
YOU EVEN STEPPED
ON HIS BEAUTIFUL FACE!
OH YOU POOR DEAR,
IT MUST HAVE BEEN SO PAINFUL.
- IT'S AWESOME, TIRIEL,
LIKE I EXPECTED!
THE SWORD IS INCREDIBLE!
- IT'S NICE TO HEAR, BUT YOU'LL
HAVE TO USE THIS SWORD FOR NOW.
WE'LL COLLECT THE OTHER ONE
SOON ENOUGH.
- RIGHT.
- I CAN SENSE IT,
IF I'M RIGHT, THE SOURCE OF
THEIR ENERGY'S SOMEWHERE NEAR.
- Tiriel: COME AND GET US.
IT'S POINTLESS!
WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
- I'M CLOSE. THE SECRET THEY
WERE TRYING TO HIDE FROM ME...
IS THERE!
- STOP FLAME HAZE!
- ALL I NEED IS ONE SECOND.
ONE BREATH,
ENOUGH STRENGTH TO STRIKE!
YOU WILL BURN!
- ( screams )
- ( laughs )
- HUH? NO!
- ( Shana screams )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: SORATH WILL DO ANYTHING
TO ACQUIRE THE NIETONO NO SHANA.
AND TIRIEL WILL DO ANYTHING TO
MAKE SURE HER BROTHER GETS IT.
WHAT DOES SHANA SEE WHEN
THE ENGULFED IN LOVE SIBLINGS
EMBRACE IN FRONT OF HER?
NEXT EPISODE, "BEHIND THE
SCHOOL WAR IS DECLARED."