- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE CRIMSON
WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( Yuji screams )
- ( roaring )
- YES, THAT'S BECAUSE YOU
ARE A THING. YOU'RE NOT HUMAN.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S NOT ONLY YOU.
EVERYONE WALKING
AROUND WITH A FLAME
IN THEIR BODY IS A THING.
THEY ARE REPLACEMENTS OF PEOPLE
WHO HAD THEIR EXISTENCE CONSUMED
BY DENIZENS OF THE CRIMSON
WORLD. THEY'RE TORCHES.
- BUT THEN,
YOU'RE SAYING WE'RE...
- THE REAL YOU HAS HAD
ITS EXISTENCE CONSUMED
AND IS NO LONGER LIVING.
RIGHT NOW
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT RESIDUE.
- I WAS ALREADY DEAD.
THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME
SHE REALLY LOOKED AT ME
WITH THOSE BLAZING EYES OF HERS,
BUT IT CERTAINLY
WOULDN'T BE THE LAST.
AS THE MEANING
OF HER WORDS HIT ME,
ALL I COULD DO WAS
STAND THERE STUNNED.
THE DAY THE WORLD CAME UNDONE,
I MET THAT GIRL OF FLAMES.
AND THEN...
I'M-- I'M DEAD.
BUT HOW?
- I TOLD YOU. A DENIZEN OF
THE CRIMSON WORLD CONSUMED YOU.
- CRIMSON WORLD?
LIKE THOSE MONSTERS?
- ( snarling )
- ( screams )
- THEY WERE RINNE, SERVANTS
OF THE CRIMSON WORLD DENIZENS.
THE WAY IT WORKS IS
THE RINNE COLLECT
AND THE DENIZENS CONSUME.
- CONSUME?
BUT YOU SHOWED UP AND SAVED ME
BEFORE THAT COULD HAPPEN,
DIDN'T YOU?
- I DIDN'T SAVE YOU.
YOU WERE JUST THERE.
IT'S NOT LIKE THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME THE RINNE AND THE DENIZENS
FROM THE CRIMSON WORLD HAVE
APPEARED IN THIS WORLD.
IN FACT,
IT'S A PRETTY COMMON OCCURRENCE.
THE REAL YOU HAD BEEN EATEN
BEFORE YOU EVEN SAW
THOSE THINGS.
- YOU'RE KIDDING.
- WELL, YOUR FLAME IS STILL
PRETTY BRIGHT,
SO IT DIDN'T HAPPEN
THAT LONG AGO.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
IT'LL BURN OUT EVENTUALLY.
- HUH?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- YOU'RE A TORCH, WHICH MEANS
YOU'RE GONNA VANISH PRETTY SOON.
EXPLANATION OVER.
- VANISH?
WAIT UP!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN...
VANISH?
THAT'S JUST NOT POSSIBLE.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
BESIDES, I'VE NEVER
HEARD OF THIS
CRIMSON WORLD PLACE OR WHATEVER.
- YES, WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE THIS
WORLD IS WHAT WE CALL SEALED.
- SEALED?
YOU MEAN THAT WAS KIND OF
LIKE A FIREWALL?
- TO BE ACCURATE, IT'S LIKE THE
SPACE YOU FIND BETWEEN WALLS.
THE FLOW OF TIME IS SUSPENDED
WITHIN THAT SPACE.
YOU'RE CUT OFF
FROM THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
NO ONE EVER REMEMBERS WHAT
HAPPENS INSIDE THERE.
ANYWAY, THE DENIZENS CONSUME
THE PERSON'S EXISTENCE,
NOT THE PERSON.
WHEN ALL IS SAID AND DONE,
IT'S AS IF THEY NEVER EXISTED.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT.
- MEANING WHAT?
- IT'S LIKE THE PERSON
HAD NEVER EVEN BEEN THERE.
OH, LOOK, PERFECT TIMING.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO SEE THAT.
THERE'S A SMALL TORCH
HEADED STRAIGHT THIS WAY.
- THE FLAME, IT'S SO SMALL.
- I KICKED THE BALL RIGHT
TO YOU.
- THAT WAS A GREAT GAME.
- YEAH, LET'S DO THAT AGAIN.
- HOW COME?
HOW COME THEY DIDN'T NOTICE?
HE JUST DISAPPEARED.
- THAT'S WHY WE
PLACE THE TORCHES.
IF SOMEONE JUST UP
AND DISAPPEARED,
THE BALANCE WOULD BE UPSET
AND CHAOS WOULD RESULT.
- ARE YOU BEGINNING
TO UNDERSTAND?
FOR EXAMPLE, IF THE GROUND
BENEATH YOUR FEET WAS
TO SUDDENLY VANISH, YOU WOULD
FALL, SUFFERING AN INJURY.
BUT IF THE GROUND
IS TRANSFORMED
INTO ICE THAT MELTS AWAY
GRADUALLY,
YOUR CHANCES OF BECOMING HURT
ARE LESSENED.
THINK OF TORCHES AS SIMILAR
TO THAT ICE.
THE EXISTENCE OF THE TORCH
GRADUALLY FADES AWAY,
AND BY THE TIME IT VANISHES...
ITS INFLUENCE HAS BEEN REDUCED
TO A MINIMUM.
IF YOU'RE STILL HAVING
TROUBLE UNDERSTANDING--
- I GET IT. I GET WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING, BUT IT'S SO--
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO REACT TO THIS?
THE PERSON I AM, YUJI SAKAI,
IS ALREADY DEAD.
THEN WHO IS THE ME THAT'S
STANDING RIGHT HERE?
- ( chattering )
- I'LL TAKE FIVE.
- Man: HERE YOU GO. THANKS.
- MMM!
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU'VE NEVER HAD THIS BEFORE?
IT'S MELON BREAD.
YOU KNOW, FOOD.
- WELL, YEAH, OF COURSE
I KNOW WHAT IT IS, BUT--
- THEN DON'T ASK.
- HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA
FOLLOW ME?
- I'M NOT. THIS IS JUST
THE WAY TO MY HOUSE.
- OH.
- I'M REALLY GOING TO VANISH.
THIS ISN'T A BAD DREAM?
- STOP MAKING ME REPEAT MYSELF.
THIS IS REALITY.
- HOW CAN THIS BE REALITY?
IT'S TERRIBLE.
- IT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS.
- THE WAY IT IS?
THIS IS REALITY?
NO, MY MIND JUST
CAN'T GRASP IT.
AND SHE'S TELLING ME THIS WHILE
SHE'S CHEWING ON MELON BREAD?
WHAT IS SHE ANYWAY?
LISTEN--
- SHUT UP, SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
YOU JUST TALK AND TALK.
- SO WHAT ARE YOU? HUMAN?
- I'M SOMETHING CALLED
A FLAME HAZE.
- A FLAME WHAT?
- A FLAME HAZE.
MY JOB IS
TO HUNT DOWN DENIZENS
THAT CONSUME EXISTENCES
AND DESTROY THEM.
- WE CAN LEAVE ALL
THE TORCHES WE WANT,
BUT THAT ONLY SERVES AS
A TEMPORARY STOPGAP.
IT DOESN'T SOLVE THE DANGER
TO THIS WORLD THAT COMES
FROM DISRUPTIONS
TO EXISTENCES.
- SO YOU'RE A FLAME HAZE.
- WE KNOW AT LEAST ONE DENIZEN
STILL USING RINNE IN THIS CITY.
- AND CONSIDERING WHAT
THE RINNE SAID,
IT COULD BE QUITE POWERFUL.
NOT LIKELY TO THINK
OF US AS A THREAT.
AND THERE'S ANOTHER REASON
WHY IT MIGHT STAY.
- THAT MYSTES
FROM EARLIER.
- HMM.
- LOOK, MARIANNE.
ISN'T IT SIMPLY BREATHTAKING?
- YES, MASTER.
- WE SHALL ACQUIRE ETERNITY
ITSELF IN THIS CITY.
IT WON'T BE LONG NOW.
- YES, BUT WHAT
OF THE FLAME HAZE?
- ( shushing )
LET US NOT RUIN THE MOMENT
WITH A VULGARITY.
THIS IS A TIME
FOR ENJOYING BEAUTY.
- MY DEEPEST APOLOGIES.
- SUCH WORDS ARE NOT NECESSARY.
THEY DISTRACT US
FROM THE HERE AND NOW.
- MASTER.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( yawning )
MAN, WAS IT ALL A DREAM?
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
- MORNING, SLEEPYHEAD.
TAKING IT EASY TODAY?
- HUH? WHAT?
IS THAT THE TIME?
- IT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
YOU ALMOST NEVER SLEEP IN.
AND YOU WENT STRAIGHT TO BED
WHEN YOU GOT HOME LAST NIGHT,
DIDN'T YOU?
IS ANYTHING WRONG?
- NO, I'M FINE, MOM.
REALLY.
HMM, THAT'S GOOD.
AT LEAST MOM'S NOT A TORCH.
- YOUR DAD CALLED LAST NIGHT.
HE'S NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO COME HOME
FOR THE GOLDEN WEEK
HOLIDAY, AFTER ALL.
- OH.
HOW WOULD MOM AND DAD REACT
IF THEY FOUND OUT
I WAS ALREADY DEAD?
TO BEGIN WITH, I GUESS
THEY WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW
THEY HAD A SON.
- BUT HE SAID HE PROMISES TO BE
HOME FOR YOUR SUMMER VACATION.
- I SUPPOSE IT'S BETTER NEVER TO
HAVE EXISTED IN THE FIRST PLACE,
RATHER THAN CAUSING THEM
ALL THAT GRIEF.
OR MAYBE I'M ALREADY GONE,
THE REAL YUJI SAKAI, I MEAN.
THEN WHAT
AM I WORRYING ABOUT?
THE REAL YUJI SAKAI WOULD BE
PRETTY DEPRESSED
OR EVEN ANXIOUS.
I FEEL KIND OF--
- SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND?
- UH. NO, NOT REALLY.
I'D BETTER GO. MY TEACHER IS
PRETTY TOUGH ON LATE STUDENTS.
LATER.
- HAVE A NICE DAY.
BE CAREFUL.
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE A LOT
EASIER TO STICK CLOSE TO YOU,
RATHER THAN RUNNING AROUND
SEARCHING FOR THE DENIZENS,
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT LIKE
OTHER TORCHES, YOU KNOW?
- OKAY.
- YOU KNOW, I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT RINNE THING
CALLED ME A MYSTES YESTERDAY.
- AHH, YOU HAVE A GOOD MEMORY.
- MYSTESES ARE TORCHES THAT
HAVE BEEN CHANGED
BY CRIMSON DENIZENS.
THEY HAVE SPECIAL ABILITIES
OR SOMETIMES THEY
CONTAIN TREASURES.
- TREASURES?
- WHEN THE FLAME
OF SOME TORCHES BURN OUT,
WHAT IS INSIDE THEM
IS TRANSFERRED
TO ANOTHER TORCH,
KIND OF LIKE THEY'RE A TRANSPORT
CONTAINER FOR TREASURES.
- WHY DO I HAVE ONE?
- DON'T ASK ME.
THE TREASURES MOVE ABOUT
ON THEIR OWN.
- Alastor: IT IS LIKELY
THE ENEMY WILL TARGET YOU
BEFORE YOUR FLAME DIMS
AND GOES OUT.
- HEY, WHAT EXACTLY
AM I ANYWAY?
- Girl: I TOLD YOU.
YOU'RE A TORCH AND A MYSTES.
BUT THE THINGS I THINK ABOUT
ARE THE SAME THINGS YUJI SAKAI
WOULD THINK ABOUT.
- OF COURSE.
BECAUSE YOU'RE HIS RESIDUE.
- I SEE.
HIRAI!
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE SAME THING HAPPENED
TO HIRAI.
HER FLAME, IT'S SO WEAK.
- YEAH, SHE WON'T BE AROUND
MUCH LONGER.
- BUT THOSE THINGS ONLY ATTACKED
HER YESTERDAY.
- THEN THEY MUST HAVE CONSUMED
MORE OF HER.
THOSE RINNE WERE FEROCIOUS,
AND THEY WERE FEEDING
PRETTY AGGRESSIVELY.
- HIRAI! HIRAI!
GOOD MORNING.
UM, HI, THERE.
- GOOD MORNING.
- IS THIS THE SAME HIRAI?
SHE'S LIKE A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT PERSON.
- BY THE END OF TODAY,
IF SHE'S LUCKY.
- LUCKY? BUT CAN'T WE
RESTORE HER SOMEHOW?
- NO. IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT'S ONLY HER RESIDUE.
THE REAL ONE IS ALREADY DEAD.
- NO WAY.
THAT'S HORRIBLE.
- WHY HORRIBLE?
THAT'S NOT A PERSON.
IT'S NOTHING MORE THAN A TORCH.
- ( scoffs )
HIRAI! WE'RE GONNA
BE LATE. LET'S RUN.
COME ON. TRY AND CHEER UP.
- WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
HE NEVER TALKED ABOUT BEING
RESTORED WHEN WE WERE
DISCUSSING HIM.
- PERHAPS IT IS A CASE
OF THINGS BECOMING CLEARER
WHEN YOU SEE IT HAPPENING
TO SOMEONE ELSE.
- ( panting )
HIRAI'S ON THE VERGE
OF DISAPPEARING?
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
DO YOU KNOW IF IKE
HAS A GIRLFRIEND?
- Teacher:
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
WELL, IT SEEMS YOU'RE LATE
FOR CLASS, SAKAI.
- SORRY, SIR.
- SAKAI, ONE DEMERIT.
- WHAT ABOUT HIRAI?
- OH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
SHE WAS WITH YOU.
NEVER MIND.
JUST TAKE YOUR SEAT.
- HMM.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU'RE ALMOST NEVER LATE.
- YEAH.
NO ONE'S EVEN LOOKING AT HER.
I CAN SEE IT HAPPENING.
HER EXISTENCE WILL KEEP FADING,
AND PEOPLE WILL JUST FORGET HER.
HIRAI, LUNCH TIME!
- WHAT?
THAT'S NICE.
- SAKAI, DID YOU ALREADY
BUY LUNCH?
'CAUSE I'M GONNA GO
STAND IN LINE.
- I'LL JOIN YOU.
HIRAI, LET'S GO TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT?
WE'LL BE WITH IKE.
YOU DON'T MIND,
DO YOU, IKE?
- SURE, FINE WITH ME.
- COME ON.
- HMM?
HEY, SATO, HAS THAT GIRL
ALWAYS BEEN IN OUR CLASS?
- SHE'S HERE,
SO I GUESS SO.
- Ike: HEY, GET THIS,
YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT,
BUT YOU KNOW MY INSTRUCTOR
AT PREP SCHOOL?
THE GUY IS MURATA'S BROTHER.
- SO DO YOU HAVE PREP SCHOOL
TODAY, IKE?
- NOPE.
GOT THE DAY OFF.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY WE HANG OUT
AT THE TRAIN STATION
AFTER SCHOOL?
YOU, ME AND HIRAI.
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE A PLAN?
- SURE.
- GOOD. IT'S SETTLED.
HIRAI, IKE'S COMING TOO.
- ( sighs )
- Yuji: SHE SEEMS
TO RESPOND A LITTLE BIT MORE
WHEN IT COMES TO IKE.
MAYBE THIS WILL HELP HER BE MORE
LIKE SHE WAS YESTERDAY.
COME ON, IKE, A LITTLE
CLOSER. SAY "CHEESE."
THAT LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
OOPS, I'M SORT OF IN THE WAY,
AREN'T I?
SORRY ABOUT THAT, HIRAI.
- HEY, SAKAI--
- WHAT SHALL WE DO NEXT?
PLAY THE CLAW GAME?
I KNOW, HOW ABOUT YOU AND IKE
PLAY A FIGHTING GAME?
HUH?
IKE, DO SOMETHING
WITH HIRAI, OKAY?
- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- HOLD ON.
- ( grunting )
- YOU'RE A DECOY,
SO TRY TO STOP MOVING.
IT'S A HASSLE IF YOU'RE
ALWAYS RUNNING AROUND.
- WHY SHOULD I HAVE TO?
- YOUR FEELING SORRY FOR IT
ISN'T GONNA HELP.
IT'S ONLY A TORCH. YOU CAN'T
STOP IT FROM VANISHING.
- BUT MAYBE IF I MAKE SURE
NO ONE FORGETS HIRAI.
- POINTLESS.
- I DON'T CARE!
- I HAVE NEVER SEEN SUCH
A FOOLISH TORCH.
- HMM.
- HEY, IKE, WHERE'S HIRAI?
- HUH?
WHO'S HIRAI?
- HIRAI.
YOU KNOW, THE GIRL YOU
WERE HERE WITH.
- WAS I WITH A GIRL?
- YEAH, SHE WAS RIGHT HERE.
NO WAY.
IS SHE GONE ALREADY?
- COME TO THINK OF IT,
I KIND OF REMEMBER
HER WALKING OUT A MINUTE AGO.
- WHAT? ARE YOU SURE?
SHE JUST WALKED OUT?
- YEAH, I THINK SO.
HEY, I JUST CLEARED THIS STAGE!
- IKE, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY ARE YOU SO INDIFFERENT?
TRY TO REMEMBER HER!
IT WAS THE THREE OF US.
WE CAME HERE TOGETHER.
COME ON, YOU KNOW HIRAI.
REMEMBER.
- DOES IKE HAVE A GIRLFRIEND
OR ANYTHING?
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE FEELING
ALL RIGHT, SAKAI?
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
- IT'S NOT IKE'S FAULT.
IT'S BECAUSE SHE'S A TORCH.
SORRY ABOUT THAT. I'M GONNA GO
AND LOOK FOR HIRAI MYSELF.
- I WONDER WHAT'S UP WITH HIM.
- HIRAI, YOU CAN'T HAVE
VANISHED ALREADY.
PLEASE DON'T DISAPPEAR YET.
( panting )
- DAMN IT. I TOLD HIM NOT
TO GO RUNNING AROUND.
HE'S ONE STRANGE TORCH.
- IT'S NOT UNCOMMON TO FIND
THOSE WHO DEFY THEIR FATE.
- HUH?
WHAT A RELIEF.
I FOUND YOU.
SORRY ABOUT IKE.
HE SAID HE HAD TO BE SOMEWHERE.
HUH? HEY, JUST
CUT OFF THE RIGHT SIDE
AND YOU'VE GOT A NICE SHOT
OF THE TWO OF YOU.
- ( inaudible )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- ( whispers )
IT'S JUST SO BEAUTIFUL.
- I SEE. SO THAT'S WHY YOU
CAME ALL THE WAY OUT HERE.
( sighs )
HIRAI, TOMORROW,
LET'S BRING IKE HERE.
YOU CAN SHOW HIM THIS
VIEW YOURSELF, OKAY?
HUH?
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS?
- Girl: THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS.
- ( sighs )
AND I WILL DISAPPEAR
IN THE SAME WAY.
- YES, JUST LIKE YOU SAW.
THE RESIDUE EVENTUALLY
BURNS OUT.
IT'S GONE, AND NOBODY WILL
REMEMBER ITS EXISTENCE.
THERE IS NOTHING LEFT.
THAT'S WHY THERE'S
NO INTERRUPTION.
- YOU'RE WRONG! I KNOW.
I KNOW THAT HIRAI EXISTED.
I KNOW SHE LIKED IKE. I KNOW
HER NAME IS YUKARI HIRAI!
THERE'S NO DOUBT SHE WAS HERE.
SHE WAS.
SHE EXISTED.
- AND YOU?
- AND I EXIST TOO.
AND I KNOW THAT
I'M YUJI SAKAI.
- YOU'RE ONLY A TORCH.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'M YUJI SAKAI.
JUST LIKE YOU'RE--
- I AM ONLY A FLAME HAZE.
NOTHING MORE.
IN A WAY,
I'M THE SAME AS A TORCH.
- WHY DO YOU KEEP SAYING "ONLY"?
JUST STOP IT.
- BECAUSE IT'S THE TRUTH.
YOU ARE ONLY A TORCH.
AND I AM ONLY A FLAME HAZE.
NOTHING MORE.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
- NO, I'M NOT.
- WHY ARE YOU SO--
- WHAT IS IT?
- YOUR NAME.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOUR NAME IS.
- I DON'T HAVE A NAME.
I'M ONLY A FLAME HAZE.
- YOU SAID IT AGAIN.
- LOOK, SHUT UP, SHUT UP,
SHUT UP!
WHO NEEDS A NAME ANYWAY?
TO DISTINGUISH ME FROM
THE OTHER FLAME HAZES,
THEY JUST CALL ME THE ONE
WITH NIETONO NO SHANA.
- NIETONO NO SHANA?
- THAT IS THE NAME OF THE SWORD
SHE CARRIES.
- NIETONO NO SHANA.
THEN YOUR NAME IS SHANA.
THAT'S WHAT I'LL CALL YOU.
YOU'RE SHANA. STOP SAYING
YOU'RE ONLY A FLAME HAZE.
AND I'M NOT ONLY A TORCH.
I'M YUJI SAKAI.
THAT'S HOW IT HAPPENED.
I'M THE ONE WHO GAVE
HER THAT NAME.
FROM THAT DAY ON, THE FLAME HAZE
WITH THE FIERY HAIR
AND BLAZING EYES WAS
KNOWN AS SHANA.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji:
A RINNE SHOWS UP AT MY SCHOOL.
PREPARING THE WAY FOR FRIAGNE,
A LORD OF THE CRIMSON WORLD.
AND IN THE CITY,
ANOTHER FLAME HAZE APPEARS.
NEXT EPISODE...