- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
ON A STROLL AT THIS LATE HOUR?
YOU'VE INDEED SAVED ME THE
TROUBLE OF DRAWING YOU OUT.
- ( screams )
- YOU WON'T SUFFER LONG.
- Tiamat: SINGLE SHOT KILL.
- INDEED, IT'S NO
USE CALLING FOR HELP.
THE FLAME-HAIRED BLAZING-EYED
HUNTER FULLY SUPPORTS
MY DECISION TO DESTROY YOU.
- ( gasps )
- SHANA SUPPORTS THIS?
- YUJI!
- ( grunts )
- ( coughs )
- HOW CURIOUS. INDEED YOU CAN
CONTROL SOME POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- Tiamat: RIDICULOUS.
- ( gasps ) SHANA!
- SHANA DIDN'T GIVE ME UP.
- Wirhelmina: WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO ACHIEVE HERE?
AFTER ALL, YOU AGREED TO
THE DESTRUCTION OF THE MYSTES.
INDEED, I ASK YOU TO MOVE
OUT OF THE WAY.
- Wirhelmina: NOW.
- Tiamat: WITHDRAW.
- Alastor: SHANA.
- ( shrieks )
- TELL ME,
DO YOU INDEED OBJECT
TO THE DESTRUCTION
OF THE MYSTES?
RANDOMLY TRANSFERRING THE
MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
TO A NEW LOCATION
WOULD INDEED ENABLE US TO
AVOID A CONFRONTATION WITH
THE BALL MASQUE.
A MAJOR BATTLE WILL
UPSET THE BALANCE OF THE WORLD.
FROM THAT PERSPECTIVE,
IT IS THE ONLY PRACTICAL CHOICE.
INDEED. GIVEN THAT WE'RE
UNAWARE OF THE ENEMY'S PLANS,
AND THAT THEY MAY, IN FACT,
ALREADY BE IN MOTION,
THIS IS OUR BEST MOVE.
BUT INDEED YOU
ALREADY KNOW THIS,
BECAUSE YOU ARE A FLAME HAZE.
ARE YOU INDEED STILL OPPOSED?
- SHANA.
- WHAT IS THIS STRANGE FEELING?
- Sydonay: HECATE, WHAT'S
THE MATTER?
- Hecate: THE PALACE OF STARS
IS TREMBLING.
- Sydonay: YEAH, BECAUSE THAT
HAG, BEL PEOL,
HAD THE CRAZY PROFESSOR FIDDLE
AROUND WITH IT.
THEY'RE PLANNING ON
ACTIVATING THE WHOLE
SACRED CHAPEL FOR REAL.
- Hecate: THE SACRED CHAPEL.
- Sydonay:
YOU'RE GOING TO BE BUSY.
SOON, YOU'LL HAVE NO
TIME FOR PRAYING.
MIGHT BE EASIER JUST TO
TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT.
- WHAT DO YOU WISH FOR?
- AN ANSWER.
I WANT THE ANSWER
TO WHAT I DESIRE.
- AND WHAT IS THAT?
- I DESIRE THE THING I DESIRE.
- ( Bel Peol chuckles )
- YOU'LL GET THE SAME
RESPONSE EVERY TIME.
IT SEEMS SHE DOESN'T
DESIRE ANYTHING.
HOWEVER, ONCE THE SACRED
CHAPEL HAS BEEN ACTIVATED,
THIS CHILD WILL BE
IN GREAT DEMAND.
- THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
BUT YOU'RE CERTAIN HECATE
WON'T BE HARMED BY THIS?
- RELAX, THOUSAND CHANGES.
HECATE WILL BECOME ETERNAL,
AND POWER OF EXISTENCE
WILL FLOW FOREVER.
- HMM, WELL, I'LL DO MY PART
TO ENSURE IT HAPPENS.
I JUST WANT TO PROTECT HECATE.
- REMEMBER, I DO NOT
BELONG TO YOU.
- MORES THE PITY. HECATE,
YOU ARE PURE AND UNSPOILED.
PLEASE STAY THAT WAY.
- IT'S ALMOST COMPLETE.
SOON I'LL HAVE ACHIEVED WHAT
NO OTHER CRIMSON LORD
HAS EVER DREAMED OF,
A FOUNT OF EXISTENCE.
- ( machine creaking )
- IF YOU HAVE NO
ANSWER FOR ME,
THEN INDEED REFRAIN FROM
GETTING IN MY WAY.
- Tiamat: DESTROY.
- THERE'S NO WAY SHANA
CAN OPPOSE THEM.
THAT'S BECAUSE
SHE'S A FLAME HAZE.
- Alastor: WAIT, SPECIALIST
OF EVERYTHING!
- ( both gasp )
- Alastor: WE'RE NOT DONE
WITH THIS MYSTES.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- Alastor: WE NEED TO HEAR HIM.
EARLIER IN THE DAY,
HE WAS TRYING TO TELL US
ABOUT A DENIZEN.
- ( gasps )
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT!
THE DENIZEN'S BIRD ORNAMENTS.
- Alastor: SHANA, YOU WERE GOING
TO ASK ABOUT THAT, WEREN'T YOU?
- UH, YEAH.
- A TRIVIAL REASON TO
POSTPONE ITS DESTRUCTION.
- Alastor: YOU CANNOT
ASSUME THIS IS TRIVIAL.
THIS MYSTES HAS AIDED US ON A
NUMBER OF OCCASIONS
WITH HIS INSIGHT.
- THAT'S RIGHT. HE HELPED US
IN THE LAST BATTLE.
I THINK IT WOULD BE WISE
TO HEAR IT.
WHAT THE MYSTES SAYS.
- WHAT THE MYSTES SAYS.
- THAT LOOK ON HER FACE.
IS IT THAT IMPORTANT?
IF YOU TWO FEEL THIS
STRONGLY ABOUT IT,
THEN I GUESS THERE MUST BE
SOME VALUE, INDEED,
IN KEEPING THE MYSTES AROUND.
I WILL POSTPONE DESTROYING
IT JUST THIS ONE TIME.
- Tiamat: ACKNOWLEDGED.
- WIRHELMINA.
- INDEED I BELIEVE YOU.
I INDEED DO NOT WISH TO
LOSE HOPE IN YOU.
- SO, WHAT I WAS TRYING
TO TELL YOU...
THE CITY'S REMAINING
BIRD ORNAMENTS...
I WAS WONDERING IF
THEY'RE STILL SAFE.
- Shana: Hmm?
THAT DENIZEN YESTERDAY DIDN'T
TURN ALL OF THEM INTO RINNES.
HE REALLY HAD NO USE FOR THEM?
- Alastor: YOU'RE SAYING
THEY COULD STILL POSE
SOME KIND OF DANGER TO US.
- WE REALLY DON'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT HE WAS TRYING
TO ACCOMPLISH, NOW DO WE?
WHAT IF WE CAN'T
FIGURE IT OUT,
BECAUSE HIS PLAN
ISN'T FINISHED YET?
- Alastor: YOU HAVE A POINT.
IT CERTAINLY IS A POSSIBILITY.
AND MORE THAN ENOUGH
REASON TO BE CAUTIOUS.
- THAT MAKES SENSE.
- WAS THAT WORTH
KEEPING ME AROUND?
- ( Shana gasps )
- Shana: I ONLY MEANT...
- I KNOW.
I'M A MYSTES, AND YOU'RE ONLY
A FLAME HAZE, RIGHT?
- SAKAI AND YUKARI.
- SHANA LISTEN, I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT I'VE MADE UP MY MIND.
- I'M GONNA LEAVE.
- HUH?
- YUJI!
- I'VE BEEN THINKING.
I'VE DECIDED I CAN'T INVOLVE
THIS CITY OR THE PEOPLE IN IT
IN ANY MORE BATTLES.
HEADING OUT ON THE ROAD IS
THE ONLY THING I CAN DO
TO HELP PROTECT EVERYONE.
- Shana: PROTECT EVERYONE.
- I WANNA PROTECT THE PEOPLE.
- FOR THE PEOPLE?
NO, THIS ISN'T WHAT I WANT.
I WANT HIM TO COME WITH ME,
BUT NOT FOR THIS REASON.
- Yuji: SO, I'M GONNA LEAVE
THE CITY.
- IT'S ALL WRONG!
BECAUSE IF YOU LEAVE, UM, BALL
MASQUE WILL STILL CHASE YOU,
OR YOU COULD BE TRACKED
DOWN BY OTHER DENIZENS.
- SO I'LL CHANGE LOCATIONS,
OR I'LL FIGHT BACK.
- YOU CAN'T!
- WHY NOT?
- YOU CAN'T, BECAUSE YOU CAN'T.
- Yuji: YOU'RE TELLING ME I
SHOULD STAY HERE?
- Shana: I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
- Yuji: WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- I BET YOU'RE GOING TO
DESTROY ME, AREN'T YOU?
- Shana: NO!
- I MEAN THAT'S WHAT ANY OTHER
FLAME HAZE WOULD DO
WHEN FACED WITH THIS
PROBLEM, ISN'T IT?
- NO, YOU'RE WRONG!
THAT'S NOT IT!
- THEN WHAT ELSE AM
I SUPPOSED TO DO?
SHANA I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S
GOING THROUGH YOUR HEAD.
- YUJI.
- Yoshida: SAKAI.
- YOSHIDA, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT THIS LATE?
- I GUESS IT'S BECAUSE OF THE
SPECIAL AMULET, THAT'S WHY.
- I SEE. YOU FELT THE SEAL.
- SAKAI, ARE YOU REALLY...
ARE YOU REALLY THINKING
OF LEAVING HERE?
- YOU OVERHEARD ME?
- I'M SORRY.
- YEAH, IT'S TRUE.
- BUT WHY?
- YOSHIDA, PARTLY
BECAUSE OF YOU,
I MADE THE DECISION TO LEAVE.
YOU SAID THAT I'M A HUMAN BEING.
THEN I REALIZED HOW MUCH I
WANTED TO PROTECT THE THINGS
THAT WERE IMPORTANT TO
ME AS A PERSON.
BECAUSE OF THAT DESIRE, IT
PROVES I REALLY AM YUJI SAKAI.
- BUT... YES, BUT...
- THANKS, YOSHIDA. IT REALLY
MEANT A LOT TO ME
WHEN YOU TOLD ME HOW YOU FELT.
I'M SORRY, BUT MY
MIND'S MADE UP.
- SAKAI.
- Tanaka: GOOD FOR YOU!
- Yuji: TANAKA, SATO.
- Tanaka: I HAVE TO SAY, THAT
WAS PRETTY MOVING, SAKAI.
YOU'RE ALRIGHT IN MY
BOOKS, DUDE.
- Yuji: WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- WELL, APPARENTLY WE CAN DETECT
SEALS BECAUSE OF THIS THING.
- ACTUALLY WE WERE KINDA HOPING
BIG SISTER HAD COME BACK.
- Sato: SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
I SAID WE'LL SEE IF
IT'S A DENIZEN,
AND IF IT IS WE'LL CLOBBER IT.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING MARGERY'S
NOT HERE ANYMORE?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S ALL OVER. ITS DONE.
- I SEE. MARGERY'S GONE, TOO.
- Alastor: I MUST SAY, I
SUPPORT YUJI SAKAI'S
OPINION ON THESE MATTERS.
CONCERNING WHETHER OR
NOT TO DESTROY HIM...
AND WHETHER TO
LEAVE THE CITY OR STAY...
- THAT MEANS...
- Alastor: YOU WOULD HAVE STRUCK
AT THE SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING
WITH YOUR SWORD IF I
HADN'T INTERVENED.
BUT IT'S ALSO CLEAR
YOU'RE STRUGGLING WITH
YOUR SENSE OF LOYALTY TO HER.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO DO WITH YUJI SAKAI?
- I DON'T...
- Alastor: OR RATHER, WHAT
DO YOU WANT HIM TO DO?
- ( gasps )
I WANT YUJI TO...
YUJI SHOULD...
I DON'T KNOW. I HAVE NO IDEA!
- THEY'LL KILL YOU AND SEND
THAT MIDNIGHT DOOHICKEY
OFF SOMEWHERE ELSE?
- APPARENTLY THAT WOULD MAKE
IT REALLY HARD TO FIND AGAIN.
AND WITH THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD GONE,
THERE'D BE NO REASON FOR
THE DENIZEN GROUP
BALL MASQUE TO
ATTACK MISAKI CITY.
- BUT THEN... YOU'LL DIE, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- OH, NO.
- SO, IS HIRAI, I MEAN SHANA,
IS SHE ACTUALLY GOING
ALONG WITH THIS?
- SHANA? I DON'T KNOW.
DAMN ALL THOSE FLAME HAZES!
NONE OF THEM GIVE A CRAP
ABOUT ORDINARY PEOPLE ANYWAY.
- SAKAI, IF YOU'RE GONNA LEAVE
THE CITY, I'LL GO WITH YOU.
NOTHING ABOUT THIS PLACE OR
MY HOUSE IS KEEPING ME HERE.
I'D SURE FEEL BETTER
GETTING OUT.
- OKAY, I'M WITH YA.
CAN'T LET SAKAI SUFFER ALONE,
NOW CAN WE?
- THANKS, YOU GUYS.
- BUT WE CAN COME BACK EVERY
NOW AND THEN, RIGHT?
- YOU BACKIN' OUT ALREADY?
- Tanaka: I'D LIKE
TO SEE SOME PEOPLE.
- Sato: WHAT?
- Tanaka: UH, NOTHING.
- Sato: WHATTYA MEAN NOTHING?
- Tanaka: NEVER MIND!
- Sato: MIND WHAT?
- Tanaka: JUST FORGET IT!
- SAKAI'S PRETTY SERIOUS.
LEAVING THE
CITY'S A BIG DECISION.
BUT HE'S ABLE TO TALK
ABOUT IT SO CALMLY.
AND HE TALKS SO FRANKLY
WITH YUKARI ABOUT STUFF.
I THOUGHT BECAUSE
OF WHAT HAPPENED,
I'D GOTTEN CLOSER TO HIM.
BUT HE SEEMS FARTHER AWAY
NOW THAN HE WAS BEFORE.
- JUST IGNORE HER!
- Yuji: THAT'S WHEN SHE
STARTED ACTING STRANGELY.
BECAUSE SHE'S BEEN
THINKING ABOUT DESTROYING ME.
NATURALLY, AS A FLAME HAZE
SHE SEES ME AS NOTHING
MORE THAN A MYSTES.
- I WANT YUJI TO...
- Wirhelmina: INDEED
I BELIEVE YOU.
- YO! YOU SAID THERE WAS
SOMETHING ABOUT THESE THINGS
THAT HAD YOU WORRIED,
SO WE THOUGHT WE'D COME BY
TODAY AND CHECK 'EM OUT.
- BIG FIRE, NO PROBLEM.
- RIGHT. I'M SURE IT'S JUST
MY IMAGINATION ANYWAY.
- SAKAI.
- HEY LOOK, THERE'S A MAID OVER
THERE. AND HIRAI'S WITH HER.
- SHANA.
- Wirhelmina: I MUST ADMIT
THAT INDEED THE INSTINCTS
OF THE MYSTES ARE GOOD.
IT IS TOO EASY TO OVERLOOK ITEMS
THAT HAVE ALREADY BEEN USED.
AND SO WE WILL KEEP WATCH
UNTIL THEY'VE ALL BEEN
REDUCED TO ASHES, JUST IN CASE.
- ( all grunting )
- Woman: OH, FANTASTIC!
- Sato: LOOKS LIKE IT'S FINE.
- Yuji: YEAH.
- ( people chattering )
- Tiamat: CAUTION.
- LOOKS BAD.
- Sato: AN UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM!
- Shana: BUT I DIDN'T
FEEL ANYTHING!
- Alastor: HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
- MAYBE LIGHTING THE FIRE WAS
THE SWITCH THAT TRIGGERED
THE UNRESTRICTED SYSTEM.
LOOK, THERE! THE SAME ONE!
- WIRHELMINA, SOMETHING'S
GOING TO APPEAR
RIGHT ABOVE THE SYSTEM.
- Wirhelmina: LIKE WHAT?
- Shana: LAST TIME, IT
WAS AN AIRSHIP.
- IT'S A SEAL!
- ( gasps )
- Sato: WHAT THE HELL'S THAT?
- Wirhelmna: WHY THAT'S...
- Alastor: INCREDIBLE.
- Shana: WHAT IS IT?
- Alastor: THE PALACE OF STARS!
- INDEED, THE HEADQUARTERS
OF THE BALL MASQUE.
- Alastor: JUDGE OF PARADOXES!
- BEL PEOL.
- IT'S BEEN A WHILE
FLAME OF HEAVEN
AND SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING.
EVEN YOU TWO FAILED TO
SEE THE TRUTH BEHIND
THE DOUBLE LAYER WE SET UP.
- OH MY! FLAME HAZES
ARE ALWAYS SO EAGER TO FIGHT.
- SHE'S PART OF BALL MASQUE!
- Alastor: BEL PEOL,
SURELY YOU KNOW WHAT A
MAJOR INTERVENTION LIKE THIS
DOES TO THE BALANCE
OF THE WORLD.
- Bel Peol: YOU CONSIDER
THIS MAJOR?
THAT JUST GOES TO SHOW
HOW FAR YOU'VE FALLEN,
FLAME OF HEAVEN.
THE REAL INTERVENTION IS
ABOUT TO BEGIN RIGHT NOW.
SO JUST SIT BACK AND
WATCH THE SHOW
AS THIS CITY BECOMES
A FOUNT OF EXISTENCE.
- Alastor: A FOUNT OF EXISTENCE?
YOU MEAN...
- ( chuckles ) Bel Peol: OH YES!
- Alastor: HOW COULD YOU?
- THERE'S SOMETHING ODD HERE.
IT'S NOT LIKE HER TO COME
OUT AND BRAG ABOUT HER PLANS.
- LOOK, THERE IT IS.
- HOW CARELESS! THEY ARE AFTER
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- Tiamat: DESTROY.
- WIRHELMINA, DON'T DO IT!
- SYDONAY!
- YOU ALWAYS WERE A SHARP ONE.
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, MYSTES.
YOU'RE THE ONE I CAME TO SEE.
- I MUST DESTROY IT
BEFORE THEY GET IT!
- SHANA!
- ( gasps )
- DID SHE JUST PROTECT
THE MYSTES? HOW RIDICULOUS.
- Yuji:
SHANA! SHANA!
- ( panting )
- BUT WHY?
- YUJI. I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: YUJI IS TAKEN TO THE
PALACE OF STARS,
WHERE THE MIDNIGHT LOST
CHILD ATTRACTS DANGER.
WITH HER FRIENDS
COUNTING ON HER,
SHANA HAS TO MAKE AN
IMPORTANT DECISION.
NEXT EPISODE, "THE
FLICKERING FLAME."