- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
HESITATION AND MERCY ARE
UNNECESSARY PERSONA GOD VESSEL.
- Tiamat: UNDERSTOOD.
- NO DEFECTS
- Tiamat: CHECKED.
COMMENCE.
- DAMN!
- Tiamat: GOAL ACHIEVED.
- THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN
DO FROM HERE ON.
ALASTOR AND I WILL GO
AND TAKE CARE OF THE REST.
FIND THE MOST FLAWLESS AND
SUITABLE FLAME HAZE
THAT YOU CAN.
CONSIDER THIS THE FINAL
REQUEST OF A WOMAN
GETTING READY TO END HER LIFE.
FAREWELL WIRHELMINA, TIAMAT.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
MAY FORTUNE AND GOOD LUCK
FOREVER SMILE UPON YOU.
- THOUSAND ORDINANCES.
THE FLAMING-HAIRED BLAZING-EYED
HUNTER'S CONTRACT
IS INDEED NOW IN EFFECT.
- Orgon: FLAMING-HAIR
BLAZING-EYES?
- HOWEVER, HER EXISTENCE
MUST BE KEPT A SECRET
UNTIL SHE BECOMES ACCUSTOMED
TO THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
OBVIOUSLY I CANNOT AFFORD TO
LET YOU ESCAPE THIS PALACE.
- Orgon: ESCAPE? YOU
CAN'T DEFEAT ME.
- YOU WILL BE FIGHTING
SOMEONE ELSE.
NEITHER I, NOR THE BLAZING-EYED
HUNTER WILL BE YOUR OPPONENT.
- Orgon: A RAINBOW?
- IT CAN'T BE.
IT...IT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
RAINBOW WINGS, MERIHIM.
- IS THIS TO BE
MY TASK, THEN?
- YOUR SKILLS ARE RUSTY.
WE WOULD HAVE YOU PRACTICE
BEFORE THE GREAT BATTLE
THAT INDEED
FULFILLS YOUR PLEDGE.
- SO THIS TO GET ME
BACK INTO SHAPE?
LONG TIME NO SEE, ORGON
- Orgon: HOW?
- Shiro: YOU WILL BE
A WORTHY OPPONENT
ON WHICH TO TEST THE POWER
OF MY RAINBOW SKY SWORD.
- BUT... HOW?
- NOW. LET'S GET
STARTED. SHALL WE?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- DO YOU REMEMBER...
THAT DAY WHEN WE BEGAN
OUR CONTRACT?
IT HAD NOTHING TO
DO WITH FATE.
I CHOSE IT OF MY
OWN FREE WILL.
- Shana: I DECIDED THAT THIS IS
RIGHT FOR ME. THIS IS MY PATH.
- DAMMIT, THIS IS TOO MUCH.
I'VE GOTTA GET AWAY FROM HERE.
- I WILL FIGHT
THE MIGHTY WARRIOR.
- WAIT! NO! DON'T!
- ( screaming )
- I'M READY.
- MIGHTY WARRIOR.
- WATCH IT!
SAW IT!
- ( grunts )
I SAW THAT!
I CAN FEEL THE
STRENGTH WITHIN ME.
THIS, THIS IS WHAT IT MEANS TO
BE A FLAME HAZE.
IT'S INCREDIBLE!
I REALLY AM FIGHTING
FOR MY LIFE.
EVEN A MONSTER LIKE HIM HAS TO
HAVE SOME KIND OF WEAK POINT.
HOW'S THAT?
A LITTLE MORE
AND HE'S FINISHED.
- Alastor: GET AWAY.
- NO, I'M TRAPPED.
WHAT'S THIS?
- Alastor: YOUR NIGHT CAPE.
AN UNRESTRICTED METHOD IN
THE FORM OF A BLACK CLOAK.
IT IS THE GARMENT OF THE
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
- MY QUEST TO HAND OVER THE
BLADE TO A WORTHY WARRIOR...
TO THAT END, I BECAME
A MYSTES,
OF MY OWN FREE WILL.
- HUH?
- Alastor: A HUMAN CHOOSING
TO BECOME A MYSTES?
- WHY WOULD ANYONE DO THAT?
- MIGHTY WARRIOR,
I HAVE SEARCHED FOR A WARRIOR
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO WIELD ME.
TO THAT END, I BECAME A
MYSTES OF MY OWN FREE WILL.
- WIELD ME?
IS THE SWORD TALKING?
- Alastor: HMM, IT SEEMS THE
THREE SEPARATE SOULS HAVE MERGED
THE ARMORED WARRIOR,
THE WEAPON ITSELF,
AND THE SWORDSMITH
WHO FASHIONED IT.
- THIS WEAPON MUST GO TO THE
MIGHTY WARRIOR
WITH THE GREATEST SKILL.
THE NEITONO NO SHANA CARRIES
THE ESSENCE OF MY LIFE.
TO THAT END, I HAVE SEARCHED
FOR THE WARRIOR WHO IS WORTHY.
- Alastor: MADNESS.
YOU'RE SAYING YOU GAVE
UP YOUR HUMANITY
ALL FOR THE SAKE OF
FINDING THIS PERFECT WARRIOR.
- Shana: I GET IT.
YOU ARE THE SAME AS ME. YOU JUST
WANNA KNOW WHERE YOU BELONG,
AND YOU DECIDED TO GO OUT AND
FIND THAT PLACE ON YOUR OWN.
WELL YOU CAN STOP LOOKING.
THE MIGHTY WARRIOR
WHO WILL WIELD YOU
IS STANDING BEFORE YOU.
- MIGHTY WARRIOR,
PREPARE YOURSELF.
- ( grunting )
FOCUS EVERYTHING ON ONE BLOW.
- ( explosion )
- WILL YOU BE GOING NOW?
- IT IS NOT A MATTER FOR
DISCUSSION, WIRHELMINA CARMEL.
I MUST FULFILL MY PLEDGE TO
HER. THAT IS WHY I AM HERE.
IS IT NOT THE SAME FOR YOU?
NO, IT'S NOT. I CHOSE THIS.
- Alastor: CLEARLY YOU'RE
OVERDOING IT.
I JUST ACQUIRED YOU.
I'M A LITTLE WORRIED THAT I'M
GOING TO LOSE
MY FLAME-HAZE SO SOON.
- I WAS LUCKY TO SURVIVE THAT.
THAT WAS A HUNDRED TIMES MORE
DIFFICULT THAN MY TRAINING.
AND A THOUSAND TIMES
SCARIER THAN THAT DENIZEN.
- YOU THINK, IT'S OKAY?
- Alastor: IT IS YOUR
RESPONSIBILITY.
- HMM. I WILL TAKE IT.
THANK YOU.
OUR JOURNEY BEGINS TOGETHER.
- Bel Peol: AH, ONE OF THEM
HAS JUST BEEN DEFEATED.
HMM...
- HUH?
- Alastor: A GREAT
CATACLYSM IS AT HAND.
- HMM...
THE CRIMSON WORLD IS HERE.
SHIRO! GET READY ALASTOR!
- ( loud explosion )
- IT LOOKS LIKE I WIN.
THE WINNER CONTROLS
THE LOSER'S FATE.
NOT THE KIND OF POWER
YOU WANT TO GIVE THE WOMAN
YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH.
PROMISE ME THREE THINGS.
YOU'LL NEVER CONSUME
ANOTHER PERSON,
YOU'LL NEVER BOTHER
THIS WORLD AGAIN.
AND THAT YOU'LL HELP
TRAIN THE NEXT
FLAME-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
DO IT TO THE VERY BEST
OF YOUR ABILITIES.
PLEASE, DO THIS FOR MY LOVE.
OUR LAST BATTLE WAS THE MOST
DIFFICULT AND MOST ENJOYABLE.
NO, I WON'T WAIT FOR YOU,
RAINBOW WINGS, MERIHIM.
THIS IS GOODBYE.
- I'VE LONGED FOR THIS,
FLAMING-HAIR BLAZING-EYES.
COME AT ME, FLAME HAZE.
- ( loud explosion )
- HMM?
- ( whimpering )
- DON'T TOUCH ME,
WIRHELMINA CARMEL.
- THERE IS A REASON WHY BOTH
OF US ARE STILL HERE.
WE ARE TO CARRY OUT
HER LAST WISH.
WE SHALL REMAIN HERE, TOGETHER,
FOR THAT REASON AND
THAT REASON ALONE.
- Wirhelmina: HE'S
SO IRRITATING.
RIGHT TO THE END,
HE GOT ON MY NERVES.
THAT HAPPENED SO LONG AGO.
INDEED, RIGHT NOW, MY SIGHTS
ARE SET ON A NEW ERA.
YES, A NEW ERA.
- ( swords clashing )
- ( grunting )
- TENMOKUIKKO'S STRENGTH
LAY WITHIN HIS SWORD.
HE WAS AN OPPONENT
AGAINST WHICH YOU
DID NOT NEED TO USE
UNRESTRICTED METHODS.
HOWEVER, AGAINST CRIMSON
DENIZENS, SUCH AS I,
YOUR OPPONENT'S ATTACKS WILL
NOT BE EVIDENT TO THE NAKED EYE.
LEARN TO KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN
WHILE SENSING THE CHANGES
IN THE POWER OF
EXISTENCE WITHIN.
YOU MUST BE ABLE TO
DETECT THE SIGN OF
AN UNRESTRICTED METHOD
BEING GENERATED.
- ( screams )
- THIS DOES NOT MEAN YOU SHOULD
NEGLECT WHAT YOUR EYES TELL YOU.
AND MOST OF ALL,
NEVER FORGET THIS.
UNRESTRICTED METHODS
BY DENIZENS CAUSE
SEEMINGLY IMPOSSIBLE SITUATIONS.
IT'S POINTLESS TO
BE SURPRISED.
FOCUS ON WHAT
IS ACTUALLY THERE.
YOU SHOULD ALWAYS BE ABLE TO
SEE US THROUGH OUR TECHNIQUES.
FOR THEY DEFINE US.
THAT IS HOW WE,
CRIMSON DENIZENS,
DO BATTLE WITH OTHERS.
THE TIME FOR TALKING IS PASSED.
- ( gasps )
- HERE I COME!
- ( inaudible )
- WIRHELMINA...
- A WHOLE NEW ERA
AWAITS YOU INDEED.
- WELL THEN, IT'S INDEED
TIME WE SAY OUR GOODBYES.
- Alastor: THANK YOU
FOR ALL YOU'VE DONE.
- NO NEED TO THANK ME.
- AREN'T YOU COMING WITH US?
- IF I JOIN YOU, ALL
MY EFFORTS UP 'TIL NOW
WILL HAVE BEEN WASTED.
- BUT...
- INDEED, FROM NOW
ON YOU'LL HAVE TO DO
EVERYTHING ON YOUR
OWN WITHOUT MY HELP.
I KNOW YOU'LL BE
JUST FINE ON YOUR OWN.
FORGIVE ME FOR INSISTING
IT BE THIS WAY.
AS LONG AS YOU ACT AS
WE HAVE TAUGHT YOU,
YOU'LL HAVE NO REAL PROBLEMS.
BESIDES, THE FLAME OF HEAVEN
IS WITH YOU NOW.
YOU INDEED HAVE NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
- Tiamat: YOU ARE READY.
- Wirhelmina: OH.
- ( sobs )
- OH, WIRHELMINA!
- I WILL BE THERE TO
WATCH OVER YOU,
SO MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
EAT TOO MANY SWEETS.
INDEED, ONE LAST HUG
BEFORE YOU GO.
- ( sobs )
- HEY, SHANA.
WHY DO YOU LOVE
MELON BREAD SO MUCH?
- WELL, YOU SEE...
- YEAH, GO ON.
IT'S A SECRET.
- ( laughing )
- UH, WAIT A MINUTE!
- SHANA, WAIT!
- Shana: FORGET IT!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN FORGET IT?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: A TUNER BY THE NAME
KHAMSIN ARRIVES IN MISAKI CITY.
THE BALL MASQUE
FINALLY MAKES ITS MOVE.
AND THE GIRL WITH FEELINGS FOR
YUJI LEARNS OF THE REAL WORLD.
NEXT EPISODE, "A NEW CHAPTER."