- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- NOW I WONDER
WHERE HE'S HIDING.
- Marco: WE'VE SEALED
THE PLACE OFF,
SO THE ONLY THING MOVING AROUND
IS GONNA BE THAT DENIZEN SCUM.
- HMM.
- THEY FINALLY FOUND ME.
- AAH!
HELLO, CORPSE COLLECTOR.
THE TIME OF YOUR DEMISE
HAS FINALLY COME.
- ( Marco laughing ) WE JUST
WANNA GIVE YOU A LITTLE KISS.
A KISS YOU ONLY GET
ONCE IN A LIFETIME.
- SHOULD I USE IT?
NO.
- OOH, THINKING OF FIGHTING?
- Marco: BRING IT ON.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE,
ALTHOUGH IT WON'T CHANGE
THE OUTCOME.
- BE CONFUSED.
- NICE.
- Marco: OH, BRAVO.
WELL DONE, WHOOPEE!
THERE'S SO MANY LITTLE BIRDIES,
WE DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS.
YEAH, RIGHT!
HYAH!
- DID YOU REALLY THINK
A PATHETIC TRICK LIKE THAT
WOULD WORK AGAINST US?
- Marco:
SAY YOUR PRAYERS, SCUM!
- HUH?
YOU LITTLE BRAT.
WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
- ALLOW ME
TO REINTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER,
THE PARTNER OF ALASTOR,
HE WHO IS KNOWN
AS THE FLAME OF HEAVENS.
I AM SHANA!
- SO SHE IS WITH THE FLAME
OF THE HEAVENS. I SEE.
- HA!  YOUR TRICK
WORKED ON US, AFTER ALL.
WITH ALL THOSE FLAPPING WINGS,
WE COULDN'T SENSE
THE LITTLE BRAT
MOVING IN CLOSER.
- Marco:
WELL, CORPSE COLLECTOR,
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY
FOR THAT TRICK!
- GET BACK.
- Lamies: IT'S YOU AGAIN.
- KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF HIM.
- HA!
LOOKS LIKE YOU BROUGHT ALONG
SOMEONE TO HELP YOU.
- Marco: A MYSTES, AND HE CAN
MOVE INSIDE THE SEAL.
- I THINK I KNOW
WHAT'S INSIDE YOU.
- LET'S TALK ABOUT IT LATER,
OKAY?
- MAKE YOUR CHOICE--
EITHER LEAVE LAMIES THE CORPSE
COLLECTOR ALONE,
OR PREPARE TO BE HURT.
- SOMEONE'S OVER-CONFIDENT.
DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES TO STOP US?
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S GONNA GET HURT HERE.
IS PROTECTING A DENIZEN
REALLY WORTH IT?
- IT IS THE DUTY
OF A FLAME HAZE.
THERE'S A RISK THE CITY
COULD BE SEVERELY DAMAGED
IF YOU DESTROY HIM.
- HE'S A DENIZEN.
IT'S MORE DANGEROUS
TO LEAVE HIM ALIVE.
- LAMIES IS HARMLESS.
- A DENIZEN
WHO DOESN'T CAUSE ANY HARM?
YOU DON'T SERIOUSLY EXPECT ME
TO BELIEVE THAT.
- I'M NOT GONNA
GET INTO AN ARGUMENT,
AND I DON'T INTEND
TO LECTURE YOU EITHER.
JUST HURRY UP
AND MAKE YOUR DECISION.
EITHER BACK AWAY
OR YOU'LL GET HURT.
- YOU LITTLE BRAT!
- ( Marco laughing )
YOU WANT AN ANSWER,
WE CHOOSE NUMBER THREE.
WE'RE GONNA KICK YOUR BUTTS!
- WE'LL KILL YOU ALL!
- WELL, YOU'RE WELCOME TO TRY.
- OH, GOOD, LOOKS LIKE
YOU'VE RAISED YOUR GAME
TO THE POINT IT'S GOING
TO BE FUN KILLING YOU.
- Marco: INDEED SHE HAS.
( laughs )
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET'S DO IT!
LET'S CREAM 'EM!
- SHANA, LOOK OUT!
- THAT WAS WELL DONE.
- HUH?
- SHE'S ANTAGONIZED THEM
TO THE POINT
WHERE THEY'RE FOCUSING ENTIRELY
ON HER AND IGNORING US.
- OH.
- SHANA.
- LET'S PLAY A LITTLE
SALLY GO ROUND THE MOON!
- ( Marco laughing )
- THAT ONE.
AAH!
- SHE GUESSED RIGHT.
- Marco: BEHIND YOU.
- Margery: SHE'S QUICK!
THINK YOU'RE SMART?
- I FEEL STRONGER
BECAUSE YUJI'S HERE.
I CAN DO ANYTHING!
- Marco: DAMN IT,
SHE WON'T STAND STILL.
DAMN IT!
- YOU READY TO GIVE UP YET?
- ( laughs )
YOU FIRST.
YOU SAID IT WAS YOUR MISSION
TO PROTECT
THAT WORTHLESS WORM LAMIES.
A FLAME HAZE'S REAL MISSION
IS TO GET RID OF THE DENIZENS.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
OUR JOB IS TO MAINTAIN THE
BALANCE BETWEEN THE TWO WORLDS.
AND TO KEEP THE BALANCE,
I'VE GOTTEN RID OF
MANY HARMFUL DENIZENS
WITHOUT HESITATION.
BUT YOU GO OUT OF YOUR WAY TO
KILL THEM, BECAUSE YOU LIKE IT!
- WHO ARE YOU TO TELL ME
WHAT'S RIGHT AND WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH, BRAT!
- YOU'RE QUITE RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOUR REASONS ARE.
AND I REALLY
DON'T CARE EITHER.
TO ME,
YOU'RE JUST A PAIN IN THE ASS.
- WHY YOU LITTLE--
( grunts )
- Marco: MARGERY, HEY!
- DON'T WORRY,
I'VE GOT IT UNDER CONTROL.
THERE REALLY IS SOMETHING
DIFFERENT ABOUT HER.
BUT IT'S NOT
HER FIGHTING STYLE,
IT'S LIKE
THERE'S SOMETHING WITHIN HER.
SOMETHING HAS GIVEN HER
THIS IRRITATING CONFIDENCE.
AH!
COULD IT BE THAT?
LET'S SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
RAIN ON THE GREEN GRASS
WHERE I CAN SEE,
RAIN RAIN EVERYWHERE,
BUT NOT UPON ME!
ATTACK!
- HUH?
THE FIRE-REPELLING RING.
- HOW DID HE SURVIVE THAT?
- Marco: HERE SHE COMES!
- AAH!
- DID YOU THINK I'D
ACTUALLY BE STUPID ENOUGH
TO LEAVE YUJI UNGUARDED?
- YOU MEAN YOU WERE WAITING FOR
ME TO TARGET HIM ALL THIS TIME?
- YAH!
- ( grunting )
- Marco: LOOK OUT,
THE UNRESTRICTED METHOD
IS COLLAPSING!
- BIG SISTER.
YOU THINK SHE PULLED IT OFF?
YOU KNOW,
GOT RID OF THAT DENIZEN?
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
- YOU WANNA GO CHECK IT OUT?
- WHY? WHAT FOR?
- AREN'T YOU THE LEAST BIT
WORRIED ABOUT HER?
- THINK ABOUT IT. WHAT WOULD BE
THE POINT OF US GOIN' OUT THERE?
SHE WOULDN'T HAVE DUMPED US
IF WE WERE STILL USEFUL.
- I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- COME ON.
- ( crashing )
- ( grunting )
- AAH!
- YOUNG MAN!
- YUJI!
- SHANA!
SHANA.
- YUJI.  AH.
YUJI, LOWER YOUR PROTECTION
WHEN I JUMP.
OTHERWISE MY FLAME WON'T WORK.
- Alastor: WAIT, IF YOU DISSOLVE
IT NOW, WE'RE AN EASY TARGET.
- YOU CAN FALL DOWN,
OR YOU CAN GET SHOT DOWN.
THIS TIME IT'S YOUR TURN
TO DECIDE.  HMM?
- WELL WELL. THIS IS A SIGHT
YOU DON'T SEE TOO OFTEN.
HMM, THOUGH I'D LOVE TO STAY
AND SEE HOW IT TURNS OUT,
I'M AFRAID I REALLY
MUST BE GOING.
- Marco: YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY
THAT EASILY!
- OKAY, DROP YOUR PROTECTION!
- AAH!
- I CAN DO ANYTHING!
SHANA!  THE BUILDING!
- Alastor: CALM YOURSELF.
SHE'LL HAVE CONTROL
IN A MOMENT.
- YUJI, YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO HOLD ON TO ME.
I CAN'T FLY LIKE THIS.
- I GOTCHA.
- HUH?
YUJI.
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
- THERE'S NOWHERE LEFT
FOR YOU TO RUN TO, LAMIES.
- Marco: THIS GAME OF HIDE AND
SEEK HAS GONE ON FAR TOO LONG.
- ( grunting )
- Marco: WHAT THE HELL?
- ( screaming )
- Margery:
BEFORE, I NEVER HAD ANYTHING
THAT WAS WORTH A DAMN.
I HAD MY LIFE, BUT EVERYTHING
ELSE HAD BEEN TAKEN.
SO I JUST WANTED
TO TEAR EVERYTHING DOWN.
I WAS GOING TO RIDICULE,
DESTROY,
STEAL AND KILL EVERYONE.
BUT EVEN THAT
WAS TAKEN AWAY FROM ME.
HE TOOK IT AWAY.
JUST BECAUSE
HE WANTED TO SHOW ME
THAT I NO LONGER
HAD ANYTHING LEFT TO DESTROY,
THAT I WAS EMPTY.
IF ONLY I COULD HURT HIM.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
JUST HIM.
- Marco:
GO ON, FINISH THE THOUGHT.
YOU'RE AN EMPTY CONTAINER,
A BEAUTIFUL VESSEL
WITH AN ULTRAMARINE FINISH.
- Margery: WHO ARE YOU?
- Marco: CALL FOR ME.
IN A MURDEROUS SHOUT,
CALL FOR ME.
MY VESSEL,
I WILL FILL YOU UP,
AND YOU WILL CARRY OUT
MY WILL.
THAT'S RIGHT, CALL FOR ME,
MY BEAUTIFUL GOBLET.
- HUH?
AAH!
( roaring )
- Yuji: WHAT IS THAT?
- Alastor:
THAT IS THE MANIFESTATION
OF THE CLAWS AND FANGS
OF VIOLATION.
- ( growling )
- HE'S RAGING OUT OF CONTROL.
AT THIS RATE,
HE'LL SHATTER THE SEAL.
- WHAT'LL HAPPEN THEN?
- YOU CANNOT REPAIR THE DAMAGE
ONCE THIS TOUCHES
THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
EVERYONE IN THE SEAL WOULD
PERISH. - EVERYONE?
- AND RIGHT NOW HIS HATRED
AND HIS RAGE
ARE SPILLING FORTH
OUT OF CONTROL.
SUCH A DISPLAY
MUST BE HAVING
SOME KIND OF EFFECT
OUTSIDE THE SEAL.
- Alastor: BUT HE'S PAST
THE POINT
WHERE HE'S WILLING
TO LISTEN TO REASON.
- THEN WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
HIT HIM UNTIL HE DOES LISTEN.
YUJI.
- I'M READY TO HELP.
JUST GIVE ME THE WORD.
- OKAY.
I'M GONNA FLY US
AS CLOSE AS I CAN.
WHEN I GIVE THE WORD,
USE THE RING TO PROTECT US.
- I UNDERSTAND.
UH, RIGHT.  I'M GONNA GRAB
ONTO YOU NOW, OKAY?
- HURRY UP!
- UH...
- I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING
IF YOU'RE THERE.
- OH, YEAH, SORRY.
AH!
MY FACE IS GETTING SQUISHED.
- THE INSTANT I ATTACK,
I WANT YOU TO PROTECT US
WITH THE AZURE RING.
WAIT FOR MY SIGN.
- Yuji: YOU THINK IT'LL WORK?
- IT WILL.
- RIGHT.
- I STILL HAVE THE FEELING
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
- ( squeals )
- DO IT NOW!
- Yuji: JUST THEN,
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I KNEW WHAT SHANA MEANT
WHEN SHE SAID TO FEEL THE KILL.
- ( object striking )
- Marco: HEY.
- I THINK I'M STILL ALIVE.
- Marco:
YEAH, YOU AND ME BOTH.
- I'M SURPRISED
YOU DIDN'T KILL US.
- I KNOW YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE HESITATED.
IT'S A GOOD THING
WE'RE DIFFERENT THAN YOU.
- BECAUSE FLAME HAZES
DON'T DO THAT?
- YES, THAT'S NOT PART
OF OUR DUTY.
I HURT YOU JUST ENOUGH TO KEEP
YOU FROM CHASING AFTER LAMIES.
I STOPPED YOU, AND THAT IS
AS FAR AS I NEED TO GO.
- YOU GO ON AND ON
ABOUT YOUR MISSION,
LIKE YOU'RE A CRIMSON LORD.
DISGUSTING.
- YEAH,
WELL, I DON'T LIKE YOU EITHER.
- HA.  WOULD YOU TWO
STOP ACTING LIKE CHILDREN?
- WHAT IS HE ANYWAY?
IT'S NOT FAIR.  ( gasps )
- DON'T WORRY. I HAVE
NO INTENTION OF HARMING YOU.
I KNOW THE CLAWS AND FANGS
OF VIOLATION WELL.
YOUR DEATH WILL BE A PAINFUL ONE
IF YOU DARE TOUCH MY GOBLET.
- Marco: SHUT UP!
NOTHING HAS CHANGED BETWEEN US.
WHAT DO I CARE
ABOUT THE BALANCE?
I'LL SWALLOW ALL
OF THE EXISTENCES AROUND HERE,
AND I'LL KILL KILL KILL
YOU ALL!
- ( sighs )
- Lamies: DON'T GO AFTER SILVER.
- ( gasps )
- Marco: BASTARD, DO
YOU KNOW WHO HE IS?
- YOU'D BE WASTING YOUR TIME.
YOU CHASE, BUT NEVER CATCH.
SEARCH, BUT NEVER FIND.
HE APPEARS AT WILL.
- NO,
I COULD NEVER STOP LOOKING.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE ASKING!
FINDING HIM IS THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERS TO ME!
- YOU WILL HAVE YOUR CHANCE TO
MEET HIM WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT.
HOW YOU ACCEPT IT AND WHAT YOU
DO THEN ARE FOR YOU TO DECIDE.
- AH.
- Alastor: CAN YOU NOT TELL US
WHO THIS "SILVER" IS?
VERY WELL,
I WON'T ASK AGAIN.
- THIS AREA HAS BEEN
QUITE SEVERELY DAMAGED.
I DON'T THINK EITHER OF YOU HAVE
ENOUGH POWER TO REPAIR ALL THIS.
- HMM.
WELL, YOU CAN USE ME.
- SO IT IS
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
BUT EVEN IF I WERE TO USE
ALL OF YOUR EXISTENCE,
IT STILL WOULD NOT BE ENOUGH.
- BUT THOSE ARE--
- Lamies: THANK YOU FOR YOUR
HELP, FLAME OF THE HEAVENS
AND FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
OR RATHER, SHANA.
- Alastor: YOU WERE A GREAT HELP
TO US AS WELL.
- THANK YOU FOR RESTORING
THE CITY TO THE WAY IT WAS.
BUT IT COST YOU ALL THE POWER
YOU'VE BEEN GATHERING.
- NEVER MIND.
I CONSIDER IT A FAIR EXCHANGE
FOR HAVING MY FAITH
IN OTHERS RESTORED.
- HOW LONG?
- WHAT?
- IT'S JUST,
I WAS WONDERING
HOW LONG IT TOOK YOU
TO GATHER UP ALL THE POWER
THAT YOU HAD TO USE UP TODAY.
- FORGET THAT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT YOU.
- HUH?
- I TAKE IT YOU'RE NO LONGER
JUST WAITING TO DISAPPEAR.
THINGS HAVE CHANGED
NOW THAT YOU HAVE
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
WITHIN YOU.
- OH, YEAH. WELL, I'M REALLY
GLAD I'M NOT GOING TO VANISH.
- NOT ONLY WILL YOU
NOT VANISH, BUT YOU--
- HUH?
- NO, THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
AND A FLAME HAZE.
I'M SURE THE BREEZE WILL BRING
ME WORD OF YOUR EXPLOITS.
UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN.
- Yuji: IS IT APPROPRIATE TO SAY
"TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF"?
- MMM.
FAREWELL, FLAME OF THE HEAVENS.
I WILL SEE YOU AGAIN
AT THE CROSSROADS OF MISFORTUNE.
- Alastor: I PRAY
THAT YOUR FLOWER OF HOPE
WILL ONE DAY BLOOM,
SPIRAL WINDHARP.
- HE'S WINDHARP?
THAT GUY?
- HUH?
WHO'S THAT?
- SPIRAL WINDHARP.
THE CRIMSON DENIZEN
WHO'S A MASTER
OF UNRESTRICTED METHODS.
HE DESIGNED A LOT OF THEM.
- REALLY?
- Alastor: CORPSE COLLECTOR
AND LAMIES ARE MERELY ALIASES.
HE USES SUCH NAMES
IN THIS WORLD
TO PROVIDE HIM WITH
THE FREEDOM HE NEEDS
AS HE PURSUES HIS GOALS,
GOALS SO LOFTY THEY ARE WORTH
SPENDING HUNDREDS OF YEARS
TO BRING ABOUT.
IT IS THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERS TO HIM ANYMORE.
- Margery: "RODE THE SEE-SAW,
MARGERY DAW,
SOLD HER BED
AND LAY ON STRAW."
- Alastor:
CHANTER OF ELEGIES,
WE ARE NOT PASSING JUDGMENT
ON YOU,
NOR DO WE SEEK
TO INFLUENCE YOU.
HOWEVER, SHOULD YOU FORGET
WHAT THE TRUE MISSION
OF A FLAME HAZE IS,
REST ASSURED,
WE WILL STOP YOU ONCE AGAIN.
- AS LONG AS WE'RE CLEAR
ABOUT THAT.
- DON'T CHASE, DON'T DESTROY,
DON'T KILL, DON'T TAKE THINGS
THAT AREN'T YOURS.
WHAT IS THERE LEFT
FOR ME TO DO?
HEY, MARCOSIAS, WE'RE SO
BEAT-UP, WE'RE LIKE A BAD JOKE.
( laughs )
I'M COMPLETELY EMPTY.
I'M WHAT THEY CALL A WOMAN
WITH A BAD REPUTATION.
- Marco: HEY!
- PLEASE DON'T SAY
SOMETHING CORNY LIKE,
"YOU'VE STILL GOT ME."
- Marco: NO, NO, LOOK BELOW.
- HMM? OH.
- IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE STILL GOT
A PLACE TO STAY.
- REMEMBER I'M STILL
NEW AT THIS,
SO YOU COULD GO A BIT EASIER
ON ME IN TRAINING.
- HEY, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO ASKED FOR LESSONS.
- YEAH, I KNOW, BUT STILL.
- SAKAI AND YUKARI--
THEY'RE TOGETHER AGAIN.
AND THEY BOTH MISSED SCHOOL
YESTERDAY.
I WONDER IF THEY'RE--
NO, IT'S JUST A COINCIDENCE.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE I'M WRONG.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: GLITTERING WATER,
BRIGHT LIGHTING--
A BATTLE TAKES PLACE
AT AN INDOOR WATER PARK.
DRESSED ONLY
IN THEIR SWIMSUITS,
THE GIRLS FACE OFF
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
NEXT EPISODE...