[theme music]
-In the-- the end,
I couldn't save you.
KIKYO: It doesn't matter.
You came for me.
That was enough.
-Kikyo.
-It's so warm.
Inuyasha?
-Kikyo doesn't want
us to mourn her.
She says She'll
protect us forever.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Sesshomaru in the Underworld.
RIN: Master Jaken, why has Lord
Sesshomaru brought us here?
JAKEN: How would I know?
For the past few
days, he appears
to have been searching
for something, though.
-If he's searching that hard,
I guess it must be important.
-Of course it is important!
-(VOICEOVER) Lady Kikyo.
The light I saw last night.
It was yours, wasn't it?
-I'm sorry, Kohaku.
I'm sorry we couldn't take
you to the priestess in time.
-It's my fault.
If only I was stronger.
Huh?
-What is it?
-Lord Sesshomaru, wait!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Huh?
-Sesshomaru.
I thought that might be you.
-Who do you think you are?
Show a little respect!
That's Lord Sesshomaru to you.
-I can only assume you have
questions about the Tenseiga
your father left you.
I can think of no other reason
you'd come visit your mother.
-M-- M-- Mo-- M-- M---
You're his mother?
-I see.
So, you were following
Naraku's scent.
-Yeah.
We figured it would
lead us to Koga.
-We wanted to get there
in time to help him fight.
-Unfortunately, we
didn't make it in time.
SHIPPO (VOICEOVER): Yeah right.
-Well, what matters
is that you came.
-I'm sure Koga must've
been relieved to see you.
-Yeah.
-It's just that Koga must
feel really frustrated
that his shards were taken away.
-Kagome, are you gonna be OK?
-Yeah.
-Wish I could see that.
My legs feel like
they're made of lead now.
I guess I just didn't
expect to survive like this.
-Mm-mm.
It's a blessing
you're still alive.
Shards or no shards,
you've helped us so much.
-Anyway.
KAGOME: Koga.
-Oh hey.
-You leaving?
-There's no sense me
sticking around any longer.
I'll only end up
holding you guys back.
-I see.
So you're leaving us too.
-Quit feeling
sorry for yourself.
Wait.
You know, I don't mean to sound
harsh, Inuyasha, (SHOUTING)
but do you think you're
the only one suffering?
Huh?
-I know.
-I mean, look at me.
Try to imagine how it feels
for me to leave Kagome behind.
You think that doesn't hurt?
-You're right.
-Would you stop
agreeing with me?
It's creeping me out!
-Wolf boy.
I'm only sitting
here listening to you
talk 'cause you're
injured, all right?
Now back off!
-Um, Koga--
-See that?
He's acting like a dumb dog.
Looks like he's got a long
recovery ahead of him.
-Look, Kagoma.
What he needs now is to
have you by his side.
-I know.
Thanks Koga.
I'm sorry to make
you worry so much.
-I know.
-You take care of yourself, OK?
-Yeah, you too Kagome.
-(VOICEOVER) Damn you, Koga.
-All right.
Bye Kagome!
-See you soon!
-You take care.
-Goodbye.
-INUYASHA: Koga!
Listen wold boy, if you
think you lost your jewel
shards for nothing,
you're wrong.
Your effort won't go to waste.
-Yeah, w I'm
holding you to that.
Kagome, feel free
to come look me up
if you get sick of the pup.
-Sure.
-Well, let's go, Koga.
-We'll run nice and
slow so you can keep up.
-Whoa!
Hang on!
-Wait up, Koga!
-And just like
that, they're gone.
-Huh?
-What is it?
-(VOICEOVER) It's coming
from above those clouds.
I can smell Sesshomaru,
and some other demon.
-Sesshomaru.
As I recall, you used to
despise humans, did you not?
And yet here you are with two
human children in your company.
Perhaps you intend to eat them.
-Tenseiga can be used to open
a path to the underworld.
Father must have told you
about it at some point.
-Oh?
Your father never spoke of it.
He simply gave me
this Meido stone.
-A Meido stone?
-He told me to use if you should
ever come to me for advice.
Oh, and he mentioned
something else as well.
As I recall, he said that
using the Meido stone
would place you in great
danger, but he told me not
to be worried or sad about that.
-She seems to be really
good at not worrying.
-(VOICEOVER) This
explains a lot.
Like mother, like son.
-What ever shall I do?
Your mother is
terribly distressed.
-Your words are
hollow, as always.
-Very well, then.
I shall have you entertain me.
-Meido Zangetsuha!
-So this is Sesshomaru's Meido.
It's nowhere near
a complete circle.
-What?
You mean Lord Sesshomaru's
sword can't cut through it?
-It's a hound from
the underworld.
At present, Sesshomaru,
it would appear
that your sword can neither
do any real harm nor any good.
Wait, Sesshomaru!
You intend to take the
path to the underworld.
For what?
To save two human children.
You have never been prone
to such foolishness.
-Nor am I prone
to it now, mother.
-Lord Sesshomaru!
Please come back!
-The tragedy here is that
none can return alive
after the path has closed.
Oh, I tried to tell him, but
he just would not listen!
JAKEN (VOICEOVER):
You wait until now
to mention this little
piece of information?
-(VOICEOVER) There it is.
A path leading straight
to the underworld.
-I can understand that
his father might've
wanted to test him,
but this is just cruel!
-Stop crying.
It's irritating.
-What will happen to him?
What will happen
to Lord Sesshomaru?
-Sacrifices are
an inevitable part
of mastering the
art of the sword.
-(VOICEOVER): Minions
of the netherworld.
Mindless creatures.
Healing Tenseiga!
INUKIMI: Minions of the
netherworld and the Meido hound
are all demons of
the underworld.
He used Healing Tenseiga
to cut them down.
-He did?
But why would Lord Sesshomaru
use healing powers?
(VOICEOVER) I've only ever
seen him do that once before,
and it was to bring
Rin back to life.
INUKIMI: Little demon.
-Huh?
You mean me?
My name is Jaken.
-What is the relationship
between the human girl
and Sesshomaru?
-Her relationship
to him, you say?
Well, based on
what I've seen, one
might say that he tends
to favor Rin over me,
despite my long years
of loyal service.
-The human girl will die.
-Huh?
-L-- Lord Sesshomaru.
-It appears that
you're able to move.
I suppose that's the power
of the Shikon jewel shard.
-The path.
-Take Rin and run away.
-OK.
Wah!
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
What lies ahead?
Is there something
at the other end
of this path that can help me
to perfect the Meido Zangetsuha?
-My lady, what will he find
when he reaches the underworld?
-I don't know.
In truth, I don't wish to know.
Once he steps into the
darkness of the underworld,
he will be finished.
Despite his powers,
not even Sesshomaru
will be able to return.
Much less those
two human children.
Sadly, there is no turning back
on the path to the underworld.
-Hey, Rin?
Lord Sesshomaru?
It's Rin.
I don't think she's breathing.
-Hm?
INUKIMI: Sesshomaru.
The darkness of the underworld
is right in front of you.
-You're sure Rin is dead?
-She isn't breathing.
And I can feel her body
getting colder and colder.
-Very well.
Set her down.
(VOICEOVER) What is
the meaning of this?
Where are the minions
of the netherworld?
INUKIMI: You cannot save
her if there are no minions
of the netherworld
for you to kill.
-Uh, does that
mean Rin will die?
-The human girl
will have to die.
-It can't be!
-Although in
theory, she could be
revived if Tenseiga
was used to cut down
the guardian of the underworld.
[gas]
-So there is hope for her yet.
-However, in actual fact,
that would never happen.
The guardian exists beyond the
darkness of the underworld,
and no one has ever
returned from the darkness.
The girl's time has come.
She cannot be saved.
-Why, Tenseiga?
Answer me!
-Please forgive me,
Lord Sesshomaru.
I was supposed to keep her safe.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
I never should
have brought her with me.
When I summoned Rin back
from the netherworld
after she was
killed by wolves, I
should have left her
in a human village.
-The darkness!
Lord Sesshomaru,
Rin's been taken.
-So he leaped into the darkness.
-Lord Sesshomaru is
my reason for living!
I'd be lost without him!
-Little demon--
-It's Jaken, my lady!
-I am not a heartless monster.
It would sadden me as well if my
son were to lose his life while
training with his sword.
I intend to open a path for him.
-You do?
I expected no less, my lady!
Huh?
-A way out.
INUKIMI: Please come
out, Sesshomaru.
If you continue
towards me, you'll
be able to exit the underworld.
However, this path I've
opened will soon close.
And once it does, you will never
able to return to this world.
-Kohaku, take this
path while it is open.
-What?
(VOICEOVER) A path is forming.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
It's Rin's scent.
-Lord Sesshomaru, wait for me.
JAKEN: So what will
happen to him now?
-That fool is no
concern of mine.
He had his chance.
-What?
-Ignoring his
mother's kind gesture.
What a spiteful child he is.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
I smell death.
-It's Rin.
-I suppose that must be the
guardian of the underworld.
-Whoa!
Whoa!
-That's the last time.
I won't have you causing
me any unnecessary trouble.
You understand?
-Yes.
(VOICEOVER) I can't
let my guard down.
If I relax for a second,
I'll be swept away.
A mountain of corpses?
[roar]
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
I'm coming for you, Rin.
[scream]
-He did it!
-Please, Rin.
You're safe now.
Wake up.
INUKIMI: That's odd.
The guardian of the
underworld has been cut down,
and yet she remains lifeless.
Little demon--
-It's Jaken, as I've told you.
But you've no intention
of remembering my name.
-Tell me, is it
possible the human girl
has been revived by
Tenseiga once before?
-She has.
Why do you ask, my lady?
-Then she cannot be
brought back to life.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
She cannot be saved?
-Is she OK, Lord Sesshomaru?
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
I cannot save her?
Tenseiga-- I let her die
for something like this.
Nothing I could have gained
was worth losing her.
Nothing at all.
-Tenseiga's glowing.
What's happening to them?
They want help.
It's like they're
pleading with Tenseiga.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
You all wish to be saved.
Is that it?
-Huh?
-The corpses of the underworld
are all being purified.
SESSHOMARU: Meido Zangetsuha!
-Huh?
He's opened another
path to the underworld!
and it is so much bigger
than it was before!
Oh, Lord Sesshomaru!
-So you've returned.
What's wrong, Sesshomaru?
You look so sad.
Tenseiga has matured
considerably,
and your Meido has expanded,
just as you'd hoped.
Isn't that cause
for celebration?
-Did you know this
would happen to Rin?
Did you, mother?
-If I'm not mistaken,
you have already
used Tenseiga to revive
her once, have you not?
Son, Tenseiga can only call a
person back from the dead once.
-Hm?
-It only makes sense.
Life is not supposed to
be limitless, after all.
It's not something that can
be renewed over and over again
for your own convenience.
Sesshomaru, had
you come to believe
that you were a god, perhaps?
That you did not need to fear
death, as long as Tenseiga
was in your hands?
You needed to learn two things.
The desire to save the
life of a loved one
taken by death, and the
sorrow and fear which
companies that loss.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
Sorrow and fear.
-Your father wanted
me to tell you this.
Tenseiga is a sword for healing.
Only a person who values
life and possesses
a compassionate heart
may wield such a weapon
and use its power to
bury their enemies.
That is the
requirement of any who
wish to be worthy of Tenseiga,
a sword that can save lives,
and condemn others.
JAKEN (VOICEOVER):
So Rin had to die
in order for Lord Sesshomaru
to learn about compassion?
-Little demon, why
are you crying?
-The name's Jaken, my lady.
It's just that Lord
Sesshomaru by his very nature
will never shed tears, so
I must cry in his stead.
-Oh.
Is that how you
feel, Sesshomaru?
This is her last chance.
You understand?
-What is that?
-It's the little
girl's life which
was left behind
in the underworld.
-Hm?
-Rin.
-You're back!
-Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru.
You're here.
-You're OK now, Rin.
-I am.
-Excuse me, my good lady.
Please allow me to thank you
on Lord Sesshomaru's behalf.
-Is Sesshomaru happy that
I've brought her back?
-Very happy, I presume.
INUKIMI: All this fuss
over a little human girl.
He's inherited one of his
father's more unusual traits.
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER):
I'll follow them.
If anyone can destroy
Naraku, it's Lord Sesshomaru.
I'm sure of it.
INUKIMI: Child.
-Hm?
-I have a question for you.
How was it you were able
to survive the underworld?
As far as I knew, that was
only possible for demons.
Never for humans.
-It's because my life is
sustained by a Shikon jewel
shard.
-I see.
Then you'd best remember this.
Your life cannot be
saved by Tenseiga.
Just as the girl was beyond
its reach, so too are you.
-Thank you.
I will remember that.
-Kikyo said that?
-Protect the last shard.
Protect Kohaku's light.
This is something
only you can do now.
-Protect his light?
What is that supposed to mean?
-I presume she wants
Kagome to purify
his shard as she
was trying to do.
-If she wanted
that, then does it
mean that Kohaku's shard can
still be used to a weapon
to defeat Naraku?
-I don't really know
what Kikyo meant by that,
and I don't know what she
wanted for Kohaku either,
but I do know she wanted us
to find him and protect him,
so I say we start looking.
All right.
Let's go.
[theme music]
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
I couldn't save Kikyo.
FLOWER PRINCE: The woman
you loved most in this world
has died, hasn't she?
You must be sad.
Sad enough to follow
her into death.
KAGOME: We encounter
the Flower Prince,
a demon that feasts on
people's sorrow and pain.
Inuyasha is lured in and
trapped by his dreams of Kikyo.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"InuYasha, The Final Act."
Flowers Drenched in Sadness.
FLOWER PRINCE: I merely showed
you the dreams you wish to see.