[theme music]
-Tetsusaiga?
-(VOICEOVER) Why does that thing
have Tetsusaiga in his hand?
-Careful.
That's no reflection.
It seems that Kanna's
mirror has actually
transformed into a demon.
It may have all the
powers of your Tetsusaiga.
Now take this.
Wind Scar!
-His Wind Scar isn't working.
-(VOICEOVER) So it did'nt
just copy the shape?
It also stole the
demonic energy?
-Your turn.
Wind Scar.
-It's real.
Get out of here!
You're too slow.
Adamant Barrage!
That doesn't work either?
-Adamant Barrage.
-Dammit.
-Fox Magic!
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Kanna's Gravestone.
-I've created a barrier.
It should keep us safe
for the time being.
-What's wrong with
your sword, Inuyasha?
How come they could
attack us, but you
weren't able to attack them?
It's almost like they've
gotten the real Tetsusaiga.
-Unfortunately, it
would seem that all
of Tetsusaiga's demonic
energy was somehow
captured by Kanna's mirror.
SHIPPO: This isn't the
first time it's happened.
That sword Dakki
was able to steal
Tetsusaiga's demonic
energy as well.
-Every time our blades across,
Dakki's demonic presence
eats away at Tetsusaiga,
absorbing its demonic energy
little by little.
Ha ha ha!
I've absorbed all the demonic
energy from the Backlash Wave.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Tetsusaiga, I
won't waste the
path you've opened!
-I've won!
SHIPPO: But in the
end, he was killed
by the demonic energy
from the blade.
-That's because he was human.
It's different this time.
-Different, to say the least.
This demon has an endless
appetite for energy.
It won't be nearly as
simple as this time.
-It seems unfair,
seeing as how far you've
come with Tetsusaiga.
-Exactly.
Who would've thought that Wind
Scar and Adamant Barrage would
fall in the hands of the enemy?
-So, is Tetsusaiga just
an empty shell now?
-Kagura.
Are you free now?
Did you ever become the wind?
Kagura.
-So has everything been
going according to plan?
-Byakuya of the dreams.
-There's only one way!
We have to defeat
the mirror demon
and take back the
demonic energy.
-Hold your horses.
Fighting against that thing
seems a bit dangerous.
-Indeed.
It would mean we'd also be
fighting against Tetsusaiga.
-Huh?
That'd be suicide!
-Relax, Shippo.
Don't be afraid.
Oh, I get it.
You're probably just realizing
what a deadly opponent I am.
-I never thought that you
were a deadly opponent, idiot!
It's the sword that
scares me, not you!
-What?
-Well, whatever it is
we're planning to do,
we better do it soon.
-No!
The red Tetsusaiga can
break through barriers.
-Hiraikotsu!
-My turn!
-Oh, you did it!
-That's not good.
The sacred arrow didn't work.
-Look at that.
They're actually
trying to resist.
[cracking]
-Kanna.
What happened to your neck?
Fine.
Ignore me, then.
-Now, Adamant Barrage.
-It's going to use
Adamant Barrage.
-It's got us trapped in here.
-No it doesn't.
-Inuyasha!
-Inuyasha, stop!
-All you've got is the
shell of Tetsusaiga.
You don't stand a chance!
-(VOICEOVER) The shell
of Tetsusaiga, huh?
We'll see about that!
I won't let you swing!
-Inuyasha!
-I'm OK.
SHIPPO: It doesn't make sense.
Look where all
these spears went.
It's like they were
trying to avoid us.
-That was Tetsusaiga.
Its protective barrier
must've kicked in.
And that means Tetsusaiga's much
more than just an empty shell.
-Inuyasha!
Look at your face!
-There's no mistaking that look.
His demon blood took over
because he was in danger.
-This is not going well.
Once Inuyasha turns
into a full demon,
he won't hesitate
to tear us apart.
In fact, he'll enjoy it!
-It's going to attack again.
-(GRAVELY VOICE) Fine by me.
Bring it on.
-Inuyasha.
Is that you?
Do you still recognize us?
-I don't know what I look
like to you right now,
but my mind is perfectly clear.
I can feel it.
Tetsusaiga is seeking
my demonic energy.
It's trying to help
me win this battle.
You're mine!
Dammit.
What's it take to
destroy this thing?
-Inuyasha's not
looking himself, is he?
In fact, he almost
looks like a demon.
[cracking]
-Kanna.
That's exactly the spot where
the mirror demon was cut.
What's going on, Kanna?
Are you somehow
absorbing the damage
inflicted on the mirror demon?
-Inuyasha.
You've turned demon
to save your own life.
How perfect.
-The Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga!
-Of course.
It's after his demon vortex!
It makes sense.
He's a mass of demonic
energy right now.
-Inuyasha, your
demon vortex will
be a pleasure to cut through.
You will be destroyed
by the very technique
that you struggled
so hard to obtain.
-Inuyasha!
-Let us help you!
-Stay away.
You come near me and
I'll cut you down too!
You don't want to know what
I'm capable of right now.
-Inuyasha.
-(VOICEOVER) This fight
is for Tetsusaiga and me.
I won't let anyone
get in the way.
-Inuyasha!
-You'll die if it goes
through your demon vortex.
-You heard him.
Now take your best shot!
Tetsusaiga's mine.
An empty puppet like you
isn't worthy of my sword!
-Yes.
-He was able to
dodge the attack.
Inuyasha's faster than
that stupid thing.
-(VOICEOVER) Even if the
demonic energy is gone,
this Tetsusaiga is
an extension of me.
This is the real one.
I cannot lose!
I got it.
What?
This thing's invincible.
That crack.
That's exactly where I
cut the mirror demon.
-It seems Kanna is taking the
damage inflicted on the demon.
-That explains why
she's all beat up.
-Kanna, you don't
have to do this.
-Please, you'll die if
you keep on fighting.
Stop now, while you
still have a chance!
-Aren't we confident to be
showing such concern for
the enemy?
-I'm saying this
fighting is unnecessary!
-Kanna, it'll only
take one more hit
and you'll be
completely destroyed.
[groan]
-Is this the shadow
of Kanna's mirror?
-Inuyasha!
-It's just too strong.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): The demon
and the sky are connected.
-Hurry up, Inuyasha!
Get out of there!
-It's no use.
He'll never outrun the shadow.
-Let's try something new.
-Unbelievable.
This time his own
attack was reflected.
-How about that?
It appears that
you're in no position
to be worrying about
Kanna after all.
-Honestly, what a
toothless bunch you are.
-Personally, the
instant I found out
Kanna was connected
to the demon,
I would have reduced
the girl to rubble,
not stopped to warn her.
Whoa, don't get upset .
That's only if I was
your enemy, of course.
(VOICEOVER) She's not upset.
She really doesn't feel
anything, does she?
-(VOICEOVER) That was too close.
I would have been a goner if
Tetsusaiga had its usual power.
Go figure.
Saved by the fact that this
demon stole its demonic energy.
Huh?
[laughter]
-Here goes nothin'!
All right.
Tetsusaiga's barrier worked.
[groaning]
-Kanna's falling apart.
-Huh?
A crack in Tetsusaiga.
-That's it.
Don't let up, Kanna.
Continue until there's
nothing left of Tetsusaiga.
Know that this is the very
purpose of your existence.
-The blade's cracking.
-Yeah, it looks
like Kanna is, too.
-Why didn't I see it?
Naraku intends for Kanna and
Inuyasha to kill each other.
-In demon form, Inuyasha
will be able to endure
this attack for a while.
But still, he
won't last forever.
-If this keeps up, Tetsusaiga
is gonna snap in half!
-Then I have no choice but
to use the Wind Tunnel.
(VOICEOVER) No.
I'd end up sucking in
the demonic energy stolen
from Tetsusaiga.
If I do that,
Inuyasha's Tetsusaiga
could never be restored.
-(VOICEOVER) This
is getting ugly.
He's not showing Kanna any
mercy, and she won't stop.
It looks like this
is the end for her.
-Kanna!
You have to stop attacking, now!
I didn't wanna have to do this.
-The shadows disappeared.
-He managed to
stop it this time.
-There are far too many
cracks in Tetsusaiga.
We need to end this
battle immediately.
-I'm taking back
Tetsusaiga's demonic energy.
If I can just cut
through this blade.
Kanna, why are you
doing this to yourself?
You won't stop me, so there's no
point in sacrificing your life.
-Of course.
Tetsusaiga takes demonic energy
from anything that it cuts.
If Inuyasha can cut
into the demon's sword,
he can reclaim the
demonic energy it stole!
-It appears they have no
intention of killing you.
For the life of me,
I can't fathom why.
I mean, Kagome could have
fired her sacred arrow
into the hole in the
sky and killed you,
but instead she chose
to warn everyone.
These people are
completely insane.
-What are you fools thinking?
Do you pity Kanna?
Is that it?
Don't you realize she cannot
feel a thing, be it pain,
or sorrow, or even fear?
Yes.
Your pity is wasted on her.
She doesn't even
understand the concept.
-Kanna, you idiot!
-Kanna!
Why are you doing this?
Inuyasha!
-He's back to normal.
-Inuyasha, you OK?
-Yeah.
I've never felt a rush of
power like that before.
Huh?
The cracks in the
blade disappeared.
Does that mean it worked?
-Tetsusaiga's back
to its old self!
-Huh?
-Kanna.
It looks to me as if
this fight is over.
-Inuyasha.
-You think he'll do it?
-You should go.
-Hm.
Another opportunity wasted.
-The mirror demon's
Tetsusaiga is gone.
Just like that.
-Kanna, I know you were
probably ordered by Naraku
to fight to the death, right?
Well, I'm not interested.
Killing you would only
give me nightmares.
-Indeed.
Any further fighting
would be pointless.
Besides.
Now she's been half
destroyed, Naraku
won't bother looking for her.
-It's true.
She may be able to survive.
-Go on, Kanna.
It's all over now.
-Over?
NARAKU: It isn't over, Kanna.
Far from it.
I've never seen
such foolishness.
Allowing Kanna to escape
after all the suffering
she caused you.
Your forgiveness and
compassion truly sickens me.
This is your final task, Kanna.
You will take the lives of
Inuyasha and his friends
with you own.
-What is it, Kanna?
Don't you understand?
You're free now.
-Free.
Kagura.
-Now walk over to
Inuyasha and his friends.
I shall be watching
over you until the end.
-It's cracking!
What's going on, Kanna?
Do you know why
this is happening?
-Move.
You must get closer
to them, Kanna.
-Huh?
I can't-- What is it
you're trying to tell me?
-Huh?
Look out!
-Kanna!
My eye!
-Kagome, are you OK?
-It's my eye!
KANNA: The light.
-Huh?
KANNA: The light
will destroy Naraku.
-It's Kanna's voice.
I can see something.
Is that the Shikon jewel?
There's a light at the center.
Kanna, are you the one
showing this to me?
This light.
Is this what will
destroy Naraku?
-There's nothing left of her.
-Nothing but fragments.
-Aw.
The poor little thing.
Naraku's got a
cruel streak in him.
I suppose I should be careful.
-So, Kanna, now you're
dead, without having killed
a single one of
them, I might add.
Do you regret your failure?
What am I saying?
How could you feel regret when
you don't even have a heart?
-You didn't have to die.
-Do you think maybe Kanna was
trying to take us with her?
Is that why she did that?
KAGOME: No.
-Huh?
-How can you be so sure?
-The truth is, she never
actually wanted to die.
That's why she wanted me
to hear her final words.
-The light will destroy Naraku.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): Kanna.
Wherever you are, I heard
your heart's last wish.
[theme music]
INUYASHA: Sango must undergo a
trial for the master of potions
to repair Hiraikotsu.
Meanwhile, Miroku risks
his life by testing
the master's strong poison.
MAN: Even if Hiraikotsu
were to be repaired,
Sango wouldn't think twice
about sacrificing it again
if it meant saving your life.
SANGO: Because I won't be
able to live if Miroku dies.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"Inuyasha, The Final Act."
Sango's Feelings,
Miroku's Resolve.
MIROKU: I want to
fight so I can survive.
So I can protect her.