[music playing]
[theme music]
NARAKU: It all began long
ago, with the simple dream
of a villain who was
clinging to life--
a prisoner in his own body.
Kikyo, to claim this beautiful
priestess as his own,
and escape this dark cave-- that
was the villain's only desire.
He fed his body to demons
to fulfill that wish.
Many demons were drawn
to the villain's body.
There they were united as one.
Thus Naraku was born.
-[grunt] Huh?
-Fool.
I have no desire
whatsoever to become human.
But I shall take the
Shikon Jewel nonetheless.
Thanks.
This jewel is about to
absorb a great deal of pain
and suffering when I use it
to slaughter the villagers.
-It's InuYasha!
-So there.
Finally, a way for me to
become all demon at last.
Ha!
-InuYasha!
-Oh!
[gasp]
-Kikyo?
How could-- I thought--
-And so I give this to
you, the Shikon Jewel,
which you must bun with my body.
It must not fall into the hands
of those who would abuse it.
[whimpering] Oh.
-Sister Kikyo!
Sister Kikyo!
-I shall take it with
me to the other world.
NARAKU: 50 years have
passed since then.
It's been a long time, Kikyo.
The Shikon Jewel
was supposed to have
been lost to the flames
that consumed your remains.
And yet it now rests
in the palm of my hand.
-(THINKING) The Shikon Jewel
has been fully defiled by Naraku
now, so much so that Magatsuhi
himself will no longer be able
to go back inside of it.
-Our fates are tied, InuYasha.
For as you and your group's
hatred towards me grew,
I consumed and
transformed your rage,
and channeled it into
the Shikon Jewel.
Now at last the defiled
Shikon Jewel is complete.
By the end of this battle,
you and your friends
will be consumed by the very
darkness you helped to create.
Kikyo's light has died.
INUYASHA: Inside Naraku.
KAGOME: Huh?
Really?
I got in?
No way!
-They wait-listed you.
But you make it.
You'll be a high school
student in the spring.
Isn't it just wonderful?
-Oh, mom.
-You should be proud, Kagome.
Wait-listed or not, you got in.
-And that's after missing
all those classes, too.
-I must be a genius.
Good morning.
-Kagome!
You made it.
-Like I'd miss your graduation.
-I guess that life
threatening illness
gave you a break for the day.
-Yeah, Kagome.
We got worried when
you didn't show up
to check you exam results.
-Tell me about it.
I totally almost cried when I
saw all or numbers up there.
-That was pretty
emotional, wasn't it?
-Yeah.
-That's great.
I'm glad to hear you made it.
-What are you talking about?
I knew we'd pass.
You were the one we
were worried about.
-I need everyone to line up.
-Oh no.
I'm too nervous to go up there.
-They say write
person on your palm
and swallow it to fight nerves.
Just do it.
It'll work.
-There.
Swallow it.
-Uh, OK.
-Let's go.
ANNOUNCER: Congratulations.
[applause]
-(THINKING) I can't believe it.
I'm graduating
from middle school.
Mom, grandpa, I have to
admit, I didn't participate
in many, well, any clubs.
But I did have a lot of fun
at the cultural festivals.
And even though only made
it to gym class a few times,
I was able to build up a
lot of stamina fighting
for my life in the feudal era.
It was painful trying to
make up for all the classes I
missed to prepare for exams.
But I managed to graduate.
-Picture time.
-Huh?
-OK, say cheese.
-Hey, Eri, let me
take the next one.
-Higurashi.
-Huh?
-It's Hojo.
-So, looks like we're going
to different high schools.
-Oh, that's too bad.
-I heard he's going to
an all boys' school.
-Oh my gosh.
I wonder if Hojo still
has a crush on Kagome.
-Probably.
-I guess no on told him
about Kagome's crazy hoodlum
boyfriend.
-Higurashi?
-Hmm?
-I'd like if we could still
stay friends, you know?
-Of course.
Let's stay friends
forever, Hojo.
-Poor guy.
-As something to remember me
by, I want you to have-- huh?
-Wow, is that really the time?
-Ah, got it.
I wanted you to have my second
button as a way to say-- huh?
Higurashi?
-I'm sorry.
But Kagome left already.
-What?
-Poor guy.
MAMA HIGURASHI: leaving
already, Kagome?
-Yeah.
-Oh, at least stay for
dinner, so we can celebrate.
-I'm sorry.
I had to beg them to let
me come in first place.
-But mom said she's making
all your favorite foods,
and everything.
-When I get back, you'll
have that graduation present
for me, right grandpa?
-I have it now.
-Really?
-Here you go, dear.
A dried dragon's tail and
tengu whiskers for good luck.
This is for graduating, and this
one here is for high school.
-Oh.
I'll just assume this
isn't my real present.
-Kagome, you worked really hard.
We're all so proud of you.
-Mom, um, thank you.
See you, grandpa, Sota.
-Please be careful.
-I will.
GRANDPA HIGURASHI: Go get 'em.
SOTA: Say hi to
the big dog for me.
-Hmm.
[dramatic music]
-The demons are on the move.
-Hmm.
It's strange.
It's almost as if they're
being drawn to something.
-Look, a demonic presence.
-Yes, it's a mass
of demonic energy.
-Hey, InuYasha, did
Naraku use the Jewel?
-Yeah, he must've.
Naraku, the light from
Kikyo that you feared
has become Kohaku's life now.
Kikyo will no longer be
able to fight against you.
And that's why
I-- no, that's why
we must defeat you ourselves.
Time to finish this,
once and for all, Naraku.
-InuYasha, thanks for waiting.
I'm all finished.
-Good.
Hope you're ready to get going.
-Welcome back, Kagome.
-That didn't take long.
-All right, InuYasha.
Let's go.
-Huh?
What happened to me?
-Awake at last.
-It's coming back to me.
We were about to leave.
Why InuYasha?
Why are you leaving me behind?
-This battle's no place
for a kid, all right?
-This isn't going to be anything
like the other battles, Shippo.
-This time, Naraku has
used the Shikon Jewel
to transform himself completely.
-That's right.
And I'm going to be
busy protecting Kagome
until her spiritual
power returns.
I won't be able to
look after you, too.
-I'm sorry, Shippo.
-Kohaku, I want you to stay here
with Lady Kaede as well, OK?
-Sister.
-Your life's a gift from Kikyo.
You mustn't waste it.
-Right.
-But why?
After being together
all this time,
aren't, aren't I a
member of this group.
INUYASHA: Of course you are.
-Am I really?
-You'll always be one
of us, Shippo, always.
Look, if we don't
come back, you'll
have to take over for us.
You understand, Shippo?
-InuYasha?
-Huh, me, by my myself?
-Of course, it can always
wait until you grow up,
and become a great demon.
You understand, Shippo?
-But still--
-You understand?
-I'll get him for this,
sucker punching me like that.
I will hunt you down!
-It's too late to
go after them now.
-Huh?
-Lady Kaede, it's growing.
-InuYasha.
-Poor Shippo.
It must be hard to
have been left behind.
-Hah.
That was quite
unexpected, hearing
InuYasha sound so sensitive.
-What?
-Indeed, all that stuff
about if we don't come back?
-Heh, I had to say
that, or Shippo never
would have agreed to it.
-Why bother if you were
just going to punch him?
-You're right.
I should have just knocked
him unconscious to begin with.
-That wasn't my point.
But this is going
to be dangerous.
My spiritual power is
still sealed by Magatsuhi.
And who knows when
it will come back.
-Well, it won't happen
until Sesshomaru
uses Tenseiga to
finish off Magatsuhi.
-You've transform, Naraku.
But you're still just a
spider to be stepped on.
Bakusaiga!
BYAKUYA: I must admit,
that new sword of yours
is really something.
-Byakuya of the Dreams.
-One swing in the
demon's direction
leaves a crumbling corpse.
And if that corpse is
reabsorbed by the main body,
it, too will crumble.
Naraku won't have a
chance, even his new form.
So by all means, sing away.
Or are you worried about
your little companion?
As you may have guessed,
she's there, inside Naraku.
-Hmm?
-Look who's here.
-That spider.
-It's Naraku.
Hold on, Kagome.
What?
-Its body is opening up?
-Huh?
Sesshomaru!
BYAKUYA: My, he
didn't even hesitate
to go in after the little girl.
Brings tears to my eyes.
-Rin's inside there?
Come on, InuYasha.
-All right.
-Sango?
-Yes, we're right behind them.
-You two are going as well?
You realize you might end
up getting eaten if you do.
-Hmm.
-Uh oh.
Going to use your
wind tunnel on me.
No.
That would accomplish nothing.
(THINKING) Though I
gladly would if my wind
tunnel weren't at its limit.
It may hold for one
or two more uses.
But after that, it will
certainly tear open.
And I will be sucked
in and destroyed.
In order to survive,
I must kill Naraku,
and break the curse of
the wind tunnel forever.
-Miroku, let's defeat Naraku.
-Yes.
And Sango, once this is all
over, let's get married.
-Huh?
Yes.
-Those fools.
If it were me, I'd much rather
sacrifice the human girl,
and destroy Naraku
from out here.
-Naraku's body is a
lot bigger than it
looks from the outside, huh?
-Yeah.
KAGOME: It's him.
-Naraku!
Yah!
-You finally made it inside.
I've been waiting for you.
[cackling]
-InuYasha!
-Huh?
INUYASHA: Will you destroy
me from the inside?
Start where you like.
Everything around you is me.
-Hiraikotsu.
-It's miasma!
-Don't tell me
you didn't notice.
The fact is, you
and your companions
have been exposed to my miasma
ever since you entered my body.
Yet curiously, none
of you have died.
Do you know why?
It is because the Shikon
Jewel desires you souls.
-Our souls?
-That's right.
It's because of your
hatred towards me,
all the rage and
despair you feel.
-That what you think?
Shut up.
I'm done talking.
It's time to settle this
once and for all, Naraku.
-It matters not what you do.
You can not change the fate
of the Shikon Jewel, which
has endured for
hundreds of years.
-Is that him, too?
-His entire body is
covered in armor.
-Well, it looks just
like the Shikon Jewel.
-Yah!
Damn.
-Now fight me, InuYasha.
We have nothing but time.
You have an eternity and
more to fight me in here.
-Tessaiga.
Huh?
Ah.
-InuYasha!
-Hiraikotsu.
-Got him.
-Hiraikotsu seems to
have worked against him.
Wait, what?
-[gasp]
Two?
-Adamant Barrage.
Damn.
It's endless.
In that case, Meido Zanhetsuha.
-A sword which sends its foes
to the depths of the underworld.
-Miroku, look.
I can see something over there.
MIROKU: The girl.
-It's Rin!
NARAKU: [menacing laugh]
It appears
the little girl is awake.
-Ha.
That's just an illusion.
NARAKU: Then by all
means, swing away.
No harm in sending this
illusion of the little girl
to the underworld.
-Rin.
-[gasp]
-Look out.
NARAKU: What are
you waiting for?
The little girl this is
Sesshomaru's companion,
not yours.
In fact, you have no
connection to her whatsoever.
And yet you're unwilling
to sacrifice her.
Well, I suspect you will
soon change your mind.
Either that, or all
of you will die.
-The Shikone Jewel, we have
to find and destroy it.
Then Naraku will die.
-The Jewel?
-What do you mean, Kagome?
-Hold on.
Didn't Naraku absorb
the Jewel already?
-Maybe not.
I sense a strong presence
from deep within Narku's body.
Which means the Jewel is
probably still in its original
for.
-Naraku hasn't
absorbed it after all.
-Ah!
-Whoa!
-InuYasha!
-Kagome!
He closed it.
-He must be trying
to split us up.
-Damn it.
Kagome, where's the Jewel.
-Huh?
That way.
-We're better off
looking for the Jewel
than trying to regroup
with Miroku and Sango.
[grunt]
-Huh?
InuYasha?
[gasp]
-[roar] [snarling]
NARAKU: Don't look so surprised.
Surely you must
have realized what
it would mean to
approach the Shikon
Jewel after I defiled it.
InuYasha is but a
weak half demon.
It seems his spirit has been
consumed by the Jewel's poison.
-Hey, snap out of it.
Ah!
-What's wrong, Kagome?
All you need to do is calm
him down, and purify him.
[chuckling] But
you can't, can you,
not as long as your
spiritual power remains
sealed by Magatsuhi.
You can not escape.
-[gasp]
-The demon form of
InuYasha will not
rest until he's ripped
your body to shreds.
-[panting]
-[growling]
NARAKU: I should
give you a present.
An arrow that's been completely
covered in my miasma.
If you use it on InuYasha,
your life will be spared.
-Do you think I'm
that stupid, Naraku?
You could never get
me to hurt InuYasha.
And he would never hurt me.
NARAKU: You think he's
not capable of it?
You will soon understand.
History will repeat
itself, Kagome.
Like Kikyo, you too will
be slain by InuYasha.
-[roar] Yah!
-InuYasha.
NARAKU: [cackling]
Poor, foolish girl.
[music playing]
SANGO: Was that really
how your father perished?
-Calm down, Sango.
KAGOME: Miroku and Sango
are tormented by illusions.
And InuYasha's
inability to save Kikyo
comes back to haunt
him, yet again.
NARAKU: You were but
a weak half demon.
InuYasha is now completely
under my control.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"InuYasha, The Final Act:
Naraku, the Trap of Darkness."
NARAKU: Forget everything
you knew-- your human heart,
and Kagome.