[music playing]
[theme music]
[sigh]
-What's the matter,
Master Jaken?
-What's the matter?
Do you not sense anything?
It is true that Tenseiga's Meido
expanded considerably after
that incident in the underworld,
but it still cannot form
a complete circle.
I suspect that is why
Lord Sesshomaru has
been impatient and
ill-tempered since.
I'm scared.
-Lord Sesshomaru,
do you wish to know
the secret behind your sword?
Do you wish to know what
Tenseiga is lacking?
-What?
-You're going to tell me
what Tenseiga is lacking.
Really?
-Yes.
I'm sure it must
trouble you greatly.
The fact that
Tenseiga's Meido has yet
to achieve a complete circle.
-How dare you?
How do you even know about that?
-Silence, Jaken.
-Who?
Me?
But I didn't say
a word, my lord.
-Why do you always lie
like that, Master Jaken?
-If you wish to
know more, then I
suggest you follow
me Lord Sesshomaru.
-Lord Sesshomaru.
INUYASHA: "A Complete Meido."
-This way.
I sense a Shikon jewel shard.
It's Kohaku.
-I can smell Sesshomaru too.
I guess the two of them
must be working together.
-That does make it harder
for Naraku to reach him.
A very wise decision.
-Kohaku.
-Lord Sesshomaru,
are you acquainted
with this odd child
we're following?
-No.
-Well then, might this not
be a trap of some kind?
-A trap?
-I don't know, promising
to reveal something
that Tenseiga lacks
and then leading
Lord Sesshomaru to his death.
-In that case, I'll
have to kill him.
-Huh?
KOHAKU: The child disappeared.
[blast]
-Hm.
-There you are.
Meido Zangetsuha!
-Master Jaken, grab this.
-Did I not just say
it might be a trap?
-You're still
alive, Master Jaken.
-Are you disappointed?
Did you want me to die?
-I see you deliberately
aimed at my footing.
Are you so desperate to learn
the secret behind Tenseiga
that you would knowingly
walk into a trap, Sesshomaru?
-Just who do you think you are?
-I do not care who you are.
Now, tell me why do you
know about Tenseiga?
-Because once, long ago,
I faced it in battle.
Although, it looked nothing like
it does now, nothing at all.
When I fought
against your father,
the sword was in
a different form.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
Against father?
-How dare you make
yourself look so young.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER): The
sword had a different form.
-Your tactics amuse me.
You fight without your sword
in order to learn its secret.
You underestimate
me, a deadly mistake.
SESSHOMARU
(VOICEOVER): The Meido.
-How did he--
-Meido Zangetsuha.
Not bad, but Lord
Sesshomaru's is bigger.
-True, but that Meido
was a complete circle.
-I'll have you know Meido
Zangetsuha was originally
my technique.
That's right.
It was mine until your
father stole it from me.
He took it along with my face.
-From what I've
heard thus far, you
summoned me here not
to reveal a secret,
but to whine about your
technique being stolen
and your face being destroyed.
-Only one practitioner is
needed for each technique,
especially considering Tenseiga
is an incomplete blade.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
Incomplete?
-Look out.
-Lord Sesshomaru!
-Well, what is this secret?
-Still curious-- even as
you approach your death?
-Very well, it appears you have
no intention of answering me.
In which case, you
are no longer needed.
-Sesshomaru, your Meido is
needlessly large and malformed.
You will never be able to create
a complete Meido like I can.
-What?
-His Meido just absorbed
Lord Sesshomaru's Meido
like it was nothing.
-Sesshomaru.
SESSHOMARU
(VOICEOVER): InuYasha.
-Kohaku.
-Sister.
-Could it be?
-Shishinki.
-What is it, Myoga?
-Huh?
You're still here?
-What did you say, Myoga?
You know the guy
Sesshomaru's fighting?
-I do.
He's known as Shishinki,
the Ogre of Death.
He's a demon who was
defeated by your father
many, many years ago.
He was a fierce
opponent as I recall.
It's impossible.
How is he still alive?
Oh dear, this isn't good at all.
If Lord Sesshomaru learns
the secret behind Tenseiga
there's no telling
what he'll do.
-Is that the old flea, Myoga?
I wasn't sure until now,
but if you're here too,
there can be no mistake.
-That is Meido Zangetsuha.
-That's it.
You're going to
regret doing that.
Wind Scar!
-So it is Tessaiga.
I heard that he had two
sons, and now here you are.
The old man gave Tessaiga
to his youngest, did he?
-Hey, Sesshomaru, what
the hell's going on here?
Why are you fighting
with this guy?
-Sesshomaru, do you
not find it strange?
Shouldn't the elder brother
have received Tessaiga.
Now, why do you suppose your
father left it to him instead?
-Such cruelty, bringing
up the one thing that
has tortured Lord Sesshomaru.
He has tried to take Tessaiga
many times without success.
He even sacrificed his arm.
He'd finally given up and begun
focusing on training Tenseiga.
And now this.
-Master Jaken, your explanation
makes perfect sense.
-But if Lord
Sesshomaru heard it,
he would make you suffer
just for saying it out loud.
-Shishinki, you summoned me
here to fight, did you not?
Then what are you waiting for?
There is no need for
all this idle chatter.
-Sesshomaru's using it too.
-And look, his is way bigger.
-Bigger, yes.
But his technique is incomplete.
-Uh, Myoga, weren't you just
with InuYasha, a minute ago?
-He ditched him.
-Sesshomaru, what do
you know of your sword?
Do you have any idea
how Tenseiga was born?
As I said, Tenseiga was
nothing like it is now.
It was in a different form
back when I fought your father.
The truth is Tenseiga didn't
actually exist at the time.
The sword I fought against
was none other than Tessaiga.
I
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Is he saying
that Tessaiga was the one
that stole Meido Zangetsuha?
-So you didn't know, Sesshomaru.
Well, let's see how
should I say this?
Tenseiga was
originally Tessaiga.
-Silence!
-Now then, I presume
the old man was
unable to control Meido
Zangetsuha after stealing it
from me, its rightful owner.
-Wow.
Is all that true, Myoga?
-Yes.
Yes.
It is true that my
Lord was pondering
how to use this technique
once he'd acquired it.
-That is why he cast
away from Tessaiga.
And so that unwanted technique,
the one Tessaiga had no use for
was given to your
Tenseiga instead.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
Unwanted technique.
-So Tenseiga was cast
off from Tessaiga.
-If that's true, it would
mean the two of them
were originally one sword.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER): Why?
Why did father do this?
-And on top of that,
if I'm not mistaken,
the younger brother
smells part human.
It seems unthinkable.
Why would the old man bequeath
Tessaiga, his original sword,
to a mere half-demon?
Poor Sesshomaru, it looks
like your father passed you
by in favour of your
younger brother.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER): Why?
Tessaiga's barrier rejects
me from even touching it.
-All right.
[growling]
-Tessaiga.
Take this!
-First, I was given
Tenseiga, a sword meant
for healing instead of fighting.
Now, I find out the
technique I finally learn,
Meido Zangetsuha, was the one
Tessaiga no longer needed.
Why, father?
Why would you treat me this way?
SHISHINKI: Do you
understand now?
Tenseiga is an incomplete sword.
It cannot perform my technique.
What you wield is just
a part of Tessaiga.
As such, it will never be able
to perform a complete Meido.
No amount of training
will change that.
-Look out, Lord Sesshomaru!
-Wind Scar.
[growl]
-So half-demon, trying to help
your older brother, are you?
Well, there's no need
to rush into battle.
I shall deal with you once
I've buried Sesshomaru.
-Shut up!
What the hell was that for, huh?
-Do not interfere.
-What's his problem?
-Well, if everything that
was just said is true,
that's a lot for
one man to bear.
-You can't blame
Sesshomaru for being angry.
-Still, if the technique
was unwanted like this guy
says, then why not just
get rid of it for good?
Instead, their father chose
to leave it in Tenseiga
and entrust
Sesshomaru with that.
MYOGA (VOICEOVER):
That he did, Kogame.
But if Lord Sesshomaru were
ever to learn the reason why
my lord left him
with Tenseiga, I
fear he would not be
able to accept it,
especially not in his
current state of mind.
-To the underworld with you.
-Shishinki's Meido is
powerful but small.
He just has to avoid it.
-How long can you keep this up?
-He can fire a bunch
of those at once?
-Stop it, Sesshomaru.
Even you won't be able
to dodge all of those.
-It would appear
that despair has
clouded your
judgment, Sesshomaru.
Well, that works for me.
-Lord Sesshomaru!
KOHAKU: We have to move
away or we'll get hit.
-You fool.
You think you can defeat
me with only your claws?
-He's doing a good
job of dodging them.
-But his movements are
becoming predictable.
-It's only a matter of time
before one of those hits him.
-Plus, it looks
like all that stuff
Shishinki said about his
father is getting to him.
He's not thinking
clearly right now.
-I must tell him what my
lord really had in mind.
It's only right that he know.
Ah, but sadly, I lack
the means to approach.
Could it be the end for him?
-I can help with that.
Now, you have the means.
See ya.
-I don't want to.
-Ha.
At least, you're
good at running away.
-You are wrong.
I have no intention of running
away from scum like you.
MYOGA: Lord Sesshomaru, please.
You must listen to
what I have to say.
I came over, because I couldn't
stay silent any longer.
-Oh.
-Lord Sesshomaru, you
were not slighted.
On the contrary, your father
bequeathed Tenseiga to you
because of who you are.
Meido Zangetsuha is
a fearsome attack
which sends one's foes
directly to the underworld.
It is not a technique
that just anyone can use.
-That is quite true.
Your half-demon
brother wouldn't be
able to endure the demonic
energy from the underworld.
-Hm.
-Knowing that you
were a true demon,
your father was betting on
your strength, Lord Sesshomaru.
You see he believed that
you would eventually
master Meido Zangetsuha
and be able to use Tenseiga
as it was intended to be used.
It was for that--
-And you would have me believe
that was his reason for casting
Tenseiga off of
Tessaiga, would you?
-Huh?
-That is a good question.
If his faith in Sesshomaru
was so great could he not have
bequeathed Tessaiga to him
along with Meido Zangetsuha.
He certainly could
have if he thought
that you were promising enough.
-Well, you do have
a point there.
-Hey, you can't let
him win the argument.
-Frankly, now even I'm
starting to feel sorry for him.
SESSHOMARU: Silence, Myoga.
There is no longer
anything to discuss.
-Lord Sesshomaru.
-Ha.
He's only got one arm.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER): I
already lost my left arm
to Tessaiga, the sword that
my father left to InuYasha.
However, I am not
one to hold a grudge.
After all, it happened
in the heat of battle.
-How dare you hit my face?
-The secret behind
Tenseiga, it is not
meant to be uttered
by a mouth as wretched
and twisted as yours.
Every word you speak
brings shame to it.
-Silence, you insolent brat.
I will make you regret damaging
my face, as your father did.
-Sesshomaru!
-I told you not to interfere.
-I don't care.
-Adamant Barrage!
-Tenseiga?
-Tessaiga?
Sesshomaru, you
should draw Tenseiga.
Try it.
Something might happen.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
What do you want?
Are you telling me to
fight alongside Tessaiga?
Worse yet, are you telling
me to help Tessaiga,
to help InuYasha.
-There's nowhere
for you to run now.
Prepare to be banished
to the underworld.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER): Tenseiga
was only cast off Tessaiga
to be rid of Meido Zangetsuha.
Now, after inheriting this
unwanted sword from my father,
I'm supposed to use
it to aid InuYasha.
-Are you ready for it?
Now, you and your
father's swords
shall spend the rest of
eternity in the underworld.
-InuYasha!
-There are so many.
-They'll never make it.
-No!
Lord Sesshomaru!
-Sesshomaru!
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
I still do not
know what father was thinking
when he gave me Tenseiga.
Perhaps, I never will, but
I no longer care about that.
Never, Shishinki.
I would not allow my life to
be taken by scum like you.
-Lord Sesshomaru's
Meido Zangetsuha
has achieved a complete circle.
-It's swallowing
Shishinki's Meido.
-It can't be.
Tenseiga is supposed
to be incomplete.
Now, I see.
I pity you, Sesshomaru.
What your father did was cruel.
It was cruel, you hear.
-Wow.
-Such immense power.
-Yeah, no kidding.
I mean just look at this place.
-Still that was too close.
A moment later, and
InuYasha and Sesshomaru
would have been banished
to the underworld forever.
-Just witnessing it
took years off my life.
-How did you get here?
-What do you know?
Myoga ended up somewhere safe.
-Again.
-Hey, uh, Sesshomaru.
That thing you just did,
that was a complete Meido
Zangetsuha, wasn't it?
Wait up, Sesshomaru.
This means you've
mastered Tenseiga now.
I can assume that, right?
Look.
Father died before I was
old enough to remember him.
I have no way of knowing what
he was thinking back then.
But all of those things
that Shishinki was saying,
that Tenseiga was something
Tessaiga didn't need,
that it's incomplete,
those were lies, right?
I mean father left you
Tenseiga because he trusted you
and because you
are a real demon.
-InuYasha.
-Why do you ask anyway?
-Why?
Because Sesshomaru,
I'm sick and tired
of you giving me trouble
about this sword.
Let's just agree that Tenseiga
was your proper inheritance
from father and let
that be the end of it.
-InuYasha is showing his
respect for Tenseiga.
-I think he's trying
to cheer up Sesshomaru.
-I hope it works.
-Can we agree, Sesshomaru?
-InuYasha, are you blind?
Can you not see it?
-See what?
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
Tenseiga was
able to produce a complete
Meido only because Tessaiga
was nearby.
They responded to one
another, and that would only
lead to conflict.
-What your father did was cruel.
It was cruel, you hear.
-InuYasha, like it
or not, you and I
are destined to fight each
other until the day we die.
Do not forget that.
-Hey.
-Please wait for
us, Lord Sesshomaru.
-Kohaku, shouldn't you talk
to your sister before we go?
-No.
We should keep up
with Lord Sesshomaru.
-Kohaku.
-Let there be no mistake,
my lord entrusted
Lord Sesshomaru with Tenseiga
because he trusted him.
However, it would appear that
Lord Sesshomaru has finally
realized my lord's true
intention for doing so.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Sesshomaru.
[theme music]
KAGOME: Sesshomaru decides
to pay a visit to Totosai
after he realizes Tenseiga's
true hidden purpose.
While he's away, Naraku
tries to make his move.
KOHAKU: Have you come for
my Shikon jewel shard.
NARAKU: With your shard, the
Shikon jewel will be complete.
I'm afraid there's nowhere
for you to run now.
INUYASHA: Next time, on
InuYasha The Final Act,
"In Pursuit of Naraku."
-Silence, Naraku.
I'm sick of listening
to your nonsense.