[theme music]
-There.
-Cut it out, will you?
-Are you leaving?
-Yes.
I've had enough.
[thunder]
-Hm?
-Oh, that's why I'm here.
-What do you want?
-I had a feeling
something was missing.
Tokijin's gone, isn't it?
-Even without the
Tokijin, my claws
would be more than
sufficient to tear you apart.
-There'll be no need
for any of that.
I had no choice
but to come here.
It was Tenseiga
that summoned me.
-Tenseiga summoned you?
-Don't play dumb with me.
I refuse to believe you
haven't noticed that Tenseiga's
been disturbed for
the past few days.
Interesting.
It appears that your
heart now possesses
what it had been
lacking all this time.
-What do you mean by asking?
-Lord Sesshomaru's
heart is flawless!
-That's right.
He's strong, and kind.
-He's never been kind to me.
-Oh, please don't
cry, Master Jaken.
-Tenseiga has reacted to
the change in your heart.
A heart that has felt rage and
sorrow not just for yourself,
but for another being.
Now you must hand over Tenseiga.
-What?
-The time has come to reforge
Tenseiga to use as a weapon.
-(VOICEOVER) Reforge Tenseiga?
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER)
Meido Zangetsuha.
-I see.
My sister took Midoriko's
dead soul, did she?
-Not only that, Kohaku's
run off somewhere.
Sango's worried about him.
She hasn't been
herself since he left.
-Forgive me.
I mustn't be very good company.
-Sango.
-You don't have to stay
with me and go have fun.
Just as long as it's
not with another woman.
-Listen.
We'll get through this together.
I'm staying here with you.
I can't even fathom leaving
you alone to go indulge myself.
-You're so kind, my good monk.
-Uh, what are you doing?
-Oh, I thought maybe you
were Shippo in disguise,
but it's really you.
I'm glad.
-I don't believe it.
She doesn't trust me?
-No, no.
'Tis the monk she does
not trust, Shippo.
-Perhaps, but that's not
what's troubling Sango.
While their
objectives may differ,
we know that both
Naraku and Midoriko
are attempting to
complete the Shikon jewel.
According to Inuyasha--
KIKYO (VOICEOVER): When
Naraku obtains the completed
Shikon jewel, it will instantly
be defiled by his touch.
In that instant, we must purify
Naraku along with the jewel.
He cannot be defeated
with a sword.
-That is what Kikyo
said to Inuyasha.
-I see.
But of course, in order to
compete the Shikon jewel,
Kohaku's life would
have to be sacrificed.
-And that's also
what Kohaku wants.
-And what of you, Sango?
Is it also your wish that
Kohaku be sacrificed?
-I don't know.
-You do not wish him
dead. 'Tis written
all over your face, my child.
-But--
-It may be a little early yet
to give up on your brother.
-Indeed it is.
-If Naraku seeks to
complete the Shikon jewel,
then we must simply
find a way to defeat him
before that happens.
Am I right?
-Miroku.
-Sango.
Regardless of what we decide
to do, we must remain united.
If you want him to live, say so.
-Thank you.
GIRL: Would you go, already?
KAGOME: I am.
Just don't push me.
-Turning in applications?
It's right over there.
-Uh, great.
Thanks.
-I so can't wait to
wear that uniform.
GIRL: Oh, man.
That was so nervewracking.
-I just wanna get
the exams over with.
-Since when are you so prepared?
-Hey, Kagome, is everything OK?
-Huh?
-Are you stressing out
because you're so behind?
-You'd better not fail.
I'm serious, Kagome!
We all have to go
to the same school.
-No problem.
(VOICEOVER) I'm
never gonna make it.
Oh, does our shrine even after
prayers for good exam marks?
-This will guarantee that
you pass all your exams.
The Shikon jewel
will grant any wish.
Long, long ago, the
priestess and the demons
engaged in a ferocious
battle over the possession
of this very jewel.
-(VOICEOVER) Yeah.
I've definitely had
enough of that stuff.
-It is said that
in the end, when
the person who obtains
the Shikon jewel makes
the one and only
correct wish, the jewel
will be purified and disappear
from this world forever.
-What is it?
The one and only correct wish?
-Well, they never told me that.
-I've never heard of it.
-Well, you never listen
to the end of the story.
-But Grandpa, that story
has absolutely nothing
to do with my exams.
-I wouldn't say nothing.
-Sure didn't seem like it did.
-I have to learn all of
these equations tonight.
Wow.
Everything's making perfect
sense all of a sudden.
Although I am kind of cold.
Cold.
So cold.
-Hey, there.
You're gonna catch a cold.
-Inuyasha?
-Huh?
-Wait.
How long?
How long have I been asleep?
A dream?
Was it all a dream?
I can't remember a thing!
-So, I take it you
didn't make much progress
with your studies?
-You could've stayed on the
other side a little longer.
-I had so much on my mind
that I couldn't concentrate.
It wouldn't have mattered
if I stayed, anyway.
-She probably couldn't,
'cause Inuyasha
was being a noisy pest.
-Hmph.
-Huh?
A fox fire.
Whoa!
KAGOME: Shippo!
A demon?
-Over there!
-My target should be
that demon's sword.
-What?
-An inn?
-I've heard of this place.
It's the demon mansion.
-Oh!
-Look, we have guests.
-You must stay the night.
-We must stay.
-What?
-To fight demons, you mean?
-I'm pretty sure that's not it.
[laughter]
-My, I've never
met a monk before.
-Well, now you have.
-Oh, so strong.
-I think you'll enjoy it here.
-What is it you think
you're doing here?
-Huh?
-What are those?
-Yes!
I jumped three ranks at once!
-And I'm up to 23rd rank!
-We made it to 25th rank.
-Thank you!
-What was that all about?
-You were just
betwitched by demons.
-Huh?
Hey, where's Shippo?
DEMON: You don't
have time for a nap.
Shape up, number 77.
-Huh?
Number 77?
Calm down.
J-j-just calm down.
-I won't lose!
-What are you doing, number 77?
-You won't get points for
attacking fellow members.
-The Demon Promotion Exam?
-Yeah.
See?
You're holding an exam ticket.
-An exam ticket?
You mean this leaf on my head?
-You've got a lot to learn.
There are 30 ranks
for fox demons.
-The highest rank you
can get is first rank.
Then there's second rank, third
rank, fourth rank, all the way
down to 26th rank.
After that you have 27th
rank, 28th rank, 29th rank,
and 30th rank, rounding
out the bottom.
That'd be you.
-It's not easy to
reach first rank.
You have to train for
over 100 years to do it.
-Tonight's guests at
the inn include a monk,
an exterminator, and a demon.
-Bewitching any one of them
will get you a lot of points.
-Those folks have no idea
that the inn is really
our examination site.
This is going to be fun.
Let's scare the
life out of them.
-Shippo!
Where are you?
-Kagome.
-Do you see that?
She's carrying sacred arrows.
She must be a priestess.
-Jackpot!
Fooling her will net
us even more points.
-Let's go.
-Hey, wait for me, you
guys! (VOICEOVER) I
can't let my friends get
hurt over some stupid exam.
Ah!
-Hey there, Shippo.
Where'd you wander off too?
-Let me go.
I don't have time
to talk right now.
-What?
Don't get cheeky with
me, you stupid little--
-Shut up!
Kagome!
-Oh, Shippo, when are you?
[laughter]
-You must fear us.
-Go on, scream for your life!
INUYASHA: Shippo!
You little freak.
-Why'd you do that?
-You have the wrong person.
-I know it's you.
Who else would do such a
crappy job transforming?
-Fail?
You'll pay for this!
-Something about them
reminded me of Shippo.
I just figured they
were his friends.
-That was one violent demon.
-How about that creepy
smile the girl was giving us
the whole time?
-Um, I just got this thing.
-Huh?
-That's impossible.
How'd you reach 25th
rank on your first exam?
-I can't believe you just
jumped up five ranks.
-Five ranks is good?
-Number 77, who are you, anyway?
-(VOICEOVER) Is it because
I beat up Inuyasha?
That must be it.
Does that mean I'll
advance in rank
every time I beat up Inuyasha?
-Number 77 knows those guys.
He shouldn't be allowed to
get points for tricking them.
-Don't you feel bad using
your friends for points?
-I do.
I really, really do.
But the exam must come first!
-Wow, that's cold blood.
-With a cutthroat
attitude like that,
number 77 is going places.
-Can you please make
it a bit brighter?
I wonder what's taking
Shippo so long to get back?
-You think he's OK?
-Don't worry about it.
He's probably still
playing with his buddies.
-Buddies?
-Yeah.
There are at least 100 of 'em.
SHIPPO: You got that
right, Inuyasha.
-Huh?
SHIPPO: And we've got you
completely surrounded.
-What are you talking about?
SHIPPO: Unfortunately,
I'm gonna need
to use you as a stepping stone.
Heh, heh, heh!
Gotcha.
-Sorry, too slow!
Ha!
-Gah!
-Did it!
Huh?
I'm still 25th rank?
But why?
Why didn't my rank go up?
-If you look closely,
you'll see it did go up.
-See?
Look right here.
If you accumulate 10 points
here, you go up one rank.
-Remember, advancing in
rank becomes more difficult
the higher you get.
-What was that for?
-I was just referring the favor!
-But we didn't do anything!
-OK, that's enough.
Sit, boy!
What's wrong with you?
They're just kids.
-Good news.
We went up a little.
-Art of crocodile tears
worked like a charm.
-Stupid brats.
-Very nice.
-Oh, I went up!
-Isn't this great?
-Hm?
[coughing]
-Let's get out of here!
-Inuyasha--
-Let me guess.
They bewitched you again?
-I can explain.
Honestly.
KAGOME AND SANGO: The
Fox Demon Promotion Exam?
-You see, the fox demon
world is quite unforgiving.
-Which is you had them transform
into women and entertain you?
-I was only trying
to help them out.
-All right, you guys.
He's out cold.
-This is almost too easy.
-Ready, and--
-I'm gonna tear 'em to shreds!
Show yourself, Shippo!
-Rawr!
-The poor things.
Their transformations
were good, too.
-Ah!
Master monk?
-Oh, look.
Dumplings.
-They look yummy.
-Hmph.
-Sango, do you really
worry about me that much?
So cute.
-Oh, Miroku--
-So cute.
-So cute--
-Yay!
More points!
-They sure know how
to exploit a weakness.
-Come on, Shippo!
You can't hide
forever, you know?
SHIPPI: I don't need
to hide from you.
I'll use my magic to crush you.
We'll see how
tough you are then.
-Oh, yeah?
Give it your best shot.
Huh?
Ah!
What were those popping sounds?
-Amazing!
That's the best
magic I've ever seen.
-That can't be the
best you've ever seen.
-Heh, heh, heh.
Wow.
Two more points and I move up.
Whoa!
Fox Magic!
Smashing Top!
What?
Take this!
Oh!
-Wake up, number 77!
It'll soon be dawn!
That's when the exam's over!
-I've still got time.
Ah!
I'm all out of jewels!
-What's wrong?
What are you waiting for?
I'm right here, if you
want to keep going.
I only needed two more points.
Well, I guess this
is my punishment.
I got so carried
away, I was actually
willing to risk my
friendship with Inuyasha
for a few lousy points.
-It's OK.
-No.
I'm so ashamed.
I'll never be able to
look you in the eye again!
-Inuyasha.
-Hm?
-You've got to go
make up with him.
-Oh, man.
Hey, Shippo--
-Heh, heh, heh.
Oh?
Yes!
-Whoa!
-He got promoted!
-Amazing!
He made 24th rank!
-I've had enough!
-Farewell, everyone!
-Don't forget us, number 77!
-His magic is legendary.
-May his story live on.
-I wonder where Shippo went?
Hm?
-Show yourself.
I know you're out there, Shippo.
You hear me?
-How do you even know he's here?
-You're not gonna
respond, you coward?
Then I'll just have
to smoke you out.
Wind Scar!
That's right.
Run away.
-(VOICEOVER) Stupid Inuyasha.
Are you trying to
kill me, or something?
Huh?
Who's there?
-My name is Mujina.
Tell me, are you with that half
demon whose blade did this?
-Huh?
Gotcha, Shippo.
You won't escape.
Wind Scar!
-Oh, no.
Tetsusaiga's demonic
energy is being absorbed.
-OK, let's go.
-I'm sorry, but
thanks to you I was
able to absorb the energy
from that half demon's blade.
-I don't understand, Mujina.
Why do you want to increase the
power of your sword so much?
Are you alone?
I mean, what about your father?
-What?
Why do you ask about my father?
-Because I smell your
father's scent on you.
-Well, he's dead now.
My father was killed
by an evil demon.
-Are you increasing your sword's
power so you can avenge him?
(VOICEOVER) That must be it.
If so, Mujina and I
have a lot in common.
This fight is no longer
about me and Inuyasha.
It's about good and evil!
Enough messing around!
-The energy was absorbed again.
-You think I don't know
exactly where you're hiding?
Huh?
-The Wind Scar didn't work.
-Ha ha.
How does it feel
to be powerless?
-Shippo, you spoiled brat.
-This isn't about us!
By helping Mujina
avenge her father,
I'm fighting for justice!
-Stand aside, Shippo.
Now it's time to test how
much demonic energy my blade's
absorbed from this half demon.
-Kagome, you should stand back.
-Wind Scar!
-Inuyasha!
-Such amazing force.
There's no chance the half
demon could have survived it.
-But why?
You said you wanted to absorb
demonic energy from his sword,
not kill him.
-I don't recall
making any promises.
-But--
-And besides, now that I have
this demonic energy on my side,
I don't plan on
sharing it with anyone.
-Not sharing it?
But I thought you were doing
this to avenge your father.
-Is that what you thought?
Actually, my father
died centuries ago.
Of food poisoning.
-She tricked me!
I never thought I'd
ever hit a girl,
but I just changed my mind!
This is for Inuyasha's pathetic
and completely pointless
death--
-Moron.
Who died a pathetic
and pointless death?
[gasp]
-Inuyasha!
You're still alive!
-But you're-- how could you
have survived that Wind Scar?
-Ha.
Maybe you need to try a
little harder this time.
-It'd be my pleasure.
Now die!
Wind Scar!
-Wind Scar?
I'd say a light breeze at best.
I don't know how much energy
your sword's absorbed,
but it's useless if the
wielder has no skill.
What should we do, Shippo?
She betrayed you, didn't she?
Should I finish her?
-I do deserve punishment.
I took advantage of
Shippo's kindness.
-Mujina--
-Our time together
was short, but I
want you to know I enjoyed
every minute of it.
-Please let me go!
If you want her, you'll
have to go through me first!
-Oh?
-Now run!
At least you can
get a head start.
-Oh, thank you, Shippo.
-(VOICEOVER) For those tears,
I'd forgive everything.
-Get going, Mujina.
-Half demon, if you want
your little friend to live,
you'll give me that
demon sword now!
-Again?
So you've finally
showed your true colors.
[groan]
-Damn you.
You've undone my
brilliant disguise.
-Who are you kidding?
You think I didn't know?
You got old geezer
stink all over ya.
-Old geezer stink?
I'm so stupid.
I thought it was her
father, but it was really
him I was smelling.
-So, what do you
want to do, Shippo?
-I don't even care anymore.
-I see.
-It's too late.
This Dakki has absorbed
all of the demonic energy
from your demon swo--
-Get lost.
-Sorry!
-Look.
The energy is returning.
-That's because
Tetsusaiga is also
a sword that steals
demonic energy.
-I'm sorry, Inuyasha.
It was all my fault.
-Don't worry about it, Shippo.
Really, it's not a big deal, OK?
-Your actions and
your words seem
to be having a bit
of a disagreement.
-(VOICEOVER) Dakki's ability
to absorb demonic energy seems
limitless, and I had
no idea until today.
Looks like I'm gonna need
to learn more about it.
-Now draw your sword.
[shout]
-A demon!
-Now let's see if it
works, Sesshomaru.
If it has truly
accepted you, Tenseiga
should guide your stroke.
-It didn't cut him.
He swung the sword, but
there's not a scratch on him.
-Master Jaken,
what is that thing?
Behind the demon.
-He's opened the path
to the underworld.
-The underworld?
What just happen?
-Isn't it obvious?
The demon's body was just
taken to the underworld.
-A technique that cuts
through to the underworld.
-It is possible
because Tenseiga is
a sword that can connect this
world with the underworld.
That is why the
master of Tenseiga
is able to see creatures
of the underworld.
Furthermore, he has the
power to bring the dead back
to this world by killing
those very creatures.
-Whoa.
He can do that?
(VOICEOVER) If only you knew.
TOTOSAI: Instead of doing
battle by wounding his opponent,
the master of Tenseiga cuts
into the path of the underworld
and sends his enemy
there for eternity.
That is how it is used.
And the name for that
technique is Meido Zangetsuha.
(VOICEOVER) He mastered
it in his first attempt.
I must admit, I'm impressed.
Spiteful brat though he may be.
But Tenseiga has spoken.
It has accepted
him, like it or not.
-What does she do?
She dies, and dies
in vain at that.
-Now that I've seen
you one last time.
-(VOICEOVER) I shall be the
one to determine if she died
in vain.
I'm ready for battle.
I know wield the
reforged Tenseiga.
-This wind--
-Let's go.
-Huh?
I'm coming.
I'm coming!
[theme music]
KAGOME: Toshu the
swordsmith has forged
a blade called Dakki that
can absorb demonic energy,
and it's about to turn
Tetsusaiga into a pile of rust.
INUYASHA: I'll take
back what's been taken.
It's not over yet, Tetsusaiga.
SHIPPO: Koga's in big trouble
when Moryomaru attacks him.
KOGA: I shall avenge the
grievances of the wolf demon
tribe!
INUYASHA: Next time on
InuYasha, The Final Act,
Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga.
Tetsusaiga, I won't waste
the path you've opened!