[theme music]
-I wonder where we are now?
-I'm not sure, but Kagome
said that the Shikon Jewel
is deep within Naraku's body.
[wind blowing]
SANGO (VOICEOVER): That's the
sound of Miroku's Wind Tunnel.
The tear must be large
for it to be so loud.
At this rate, the next time he
opens it, it may be the last.
-What is it, Sango?
-Miro-- huh?
[music playing]
Huh?
SANGO: An illusion?
Where is this?
-Master Mushin's temple.
MIROKU (VOICEOVER): Naraku,
what do you intend to show us?
Do you believe that
one of your illusions
will be able to distract
me at this point?
Huh!
My father.
[explosion]
YOUNG MIROKU: Father!
MUSHIN: No, don't go
towards him, Miroku!
You will be pulled into your
father's Wind Tunnel too
if you go.
-Father!
[music playing]
-No.
No!
MIROKU (VOICEOVER): Naraku, I've
relived this scene many times,
but it's new to Sango.
Sango, please, calm down.
-How awful.
Was that really how
your father perished?
-Sango, listen.
It was an illusion.
You mustn't let it get to you.
-How terrible.
It was such a terrible death.
MIROKU (VOICEOVER): Of course!
Naraku was after Sango, not me.
-Get up, Sango.
Staying here is exactly
what he wants us to do.
-So terrible.
NARRATOR: "Naraku--
The Trap Of Darkness."
-Inuyasha!
-Ah!
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): I never
realized it, but the two of us
had fallen into Naraku's
trap, hating and hurting
each other just as he wanted.
I had no idea that I would
end up losing her forever.
Kikyo, I promised I would
protect you this time.
I wasn't going to
lose you again.
But in the end, I
couldn't save you.
-Inuyasha.
-Huh?
K-k-kagome?
-Please just let
me stay with you.
-Kagome!
Huh?
I can smell Kagome's blood!
Did I kill her?
NARAKU: That's right,
you certainly did.
-Huh?
-Inuyasha, you changed
into your demon form.
You lost your human heart
and tore the girl apart.
You killed our beloved
with your very own hands.
-What!
-It happened again, didn't it?
Instead of protecting
your woman,
you made her the victim
of your weak heart.
[echoing] Kikyo and Kagome.
Kikyo and Kagome.
Kikyo--
-Shut up!
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
I killed Kagome?
It can't be!
It's not possible!
Ah!
Damn it.
NARAKU: Inuyasha, though you are
a half demon with a weak hear,
I shall grant you salvation.
-Ahh!
NARAKU: Forget everything
you knew, Inuyasha.
Your human heart and Kagome too.
Know only the joy of
tearing apart your prey.
That is exactly what the
Shikon Jewel desires of you.
-Mmm-- hm?
Sesshomaru?
You've been driving away
these demons all this time?
-That wound, is it
Inuyasha's New doing?
Being a mere half
demon, I presume
Narraku's darkness overcame him.
-No, that's not it!
Wait!
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): Before
he truly lost control,
I'm pretty sure Inuyasha
helped me to escape.
Isn't that right, Inuyasha?
-The more we destroy,
the more appear.
-There's no end to this!
-No, Miroku!
-Hm?
-Kirara!
We have to get away from here.
SANGO (VOICEOVER): Our
only option is to run.
If Miroku's forced to use
his Wind Tunnel again,
he'll surely die.
-Not good!
-Kirara!
-Sango!
Sango!
She won't make it!
-Miroku, don't do it!
-Wind Tunnel!
Ahhh!
-Miroku, stop!
-Stay away, Sango!
MIROKU: (VOICEOVER): I'm
going to end up like father.
[gasping]
It's subsided for now.
Still, there's no turning back.
-Miroku!
-Sango, we must part ways.
Farewell.
-Wait!
You can't!
Miroku!
MIROKU: (VOICEOVER):
Forgive me, Sango.
My Wind Tunnel will
soon tear open,
and when it does, if
you're still around me,
I won't be able to save you.
You'll be swallowed
by it along with me.
If that happened, it would be
more painful than my own death.
-Miroku!
-Sesshomaru, your nose is as
sharp as Inuyasha's, isn't it?
Aren't you able to locate Rin?
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): No answer.
Maybe I shouldn't have
mentioned Inuyasha.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
Naraku's body
is much larger on
the inside than it
appears from the outside.
KAGOME: Look!
Rin's right up there!
-That is only an illusion.
SESSHOMARU
(VOICEOVER): Pathetic.
Is Naraku's trying to mock me?
All the same, it's clear
I cannot use Bakusaiga
carelessly.
[music playing]
-Hey, what-- what
happened to me?
MAGATSUHI: [heavy sigh]
-Ahh!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Help!
Somebody!
Inuyasha!
Huh?
-[laughs]
RIN: I thought
you were Inuyasha.
-Lady Kaede, could that be him?
-Yes.
It must be Naraku's
new transformation.
Quite ominous, isn't it?
Like a giant Shikon Jewel this
has been completely defiled.
-Inuyasha.
-Look, if we don't
come back, you'll
have to take over for us.
You understand, Shippo?
-How long do I
have to wait here?
You should have let me come
with you guys, Inuyasha.
JAKEN: Hm!
You say that now.
-Ahh!
-It's easy to be
brave when you're
watching from a safe distance.
-Oh, yeah?
And tell me what are
you doing here, Jaken?
Let me guess.
You were probably hiding from
Narraku when they left, right?
-Such slanderous conjecture!
I was sitting in
the shadows deep
in thought when
Inuyasha and the others
rushed off without
even consulting me,
the tragic result
of which is that I
wasn't able to join
them in battle.
-Yeah, and pigs can fly.
[music playing]
-Shippo, you can
fly, can you not?
-Huh?
-I want you to take me up there.
You must take me up to that
big black sphere in the sky.
Yes, I belong at Lord
Sesshomaru's side.
Hey!
You can't run off by
yourself like that!
-See you later!
Ow!
Hey, what was that for?
-You dare use the
Staff of Two Heads,
a precious give from
Lord Sesshomaru!
You hit me!
KOHAKU: Excuse me.
-Huh?
-She's close by.
-What?
-We have to fly.
-You know where she is?
-Inuyasha is there with her.
-Inuyasha too?
-However he remains
in demon form.
[music playing]
-Ahh!
-Stay there!
Don't move!
-What a surprise.
Even in demon form, your
human heart remains.
However, your pitiful attacks
cannot even scratch me.
I, Magatsuhi, will show you
just tell powerless you are!
-Magatshui's entered Inuyasha!
He's trying to control him,
just like he controlled Kohaku.
-Huh!
This half demon will serve well
enough to challenge Sesshomaru.
-Oh!
Lord Sesshomaru!
Oh!
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER): Rin.
-I can't move!
-Inuyasha?
-[growling]
-Magatsuhi, you chose the
wrong person to possess.
I shall slay you
along with Inuyasha.
[shouts]
-Inuyasha, no!
-Hah!
-See, Jaken?
You could have taken A-Un
if you wanted a ride so bad.
-So why were you trying to ride
Shippo up to Naraku anyway?
-Silence, child!
What kind of fool would I have
to be to rush up here alone?
-So that was your way
of inviting him along?
But Shippo's only
a child, Jaken.
-Only a child!
Look who's talking.
You shouldn't be here, Kohaku.
Sango kept telling
you not to come.
Don't you remember?
-True, but it's too
late to turn back now.
SHIPPO: Whoa!
This thing looks a lot bigger
when you get up close to it.
-Look at that!
-Inuyasha's Meigo Zangetshua.
KOHAKU: All right, let's go.
JAKEN: What?
SHIPPO: You mean we're
going inside Naraku?
-We have to hurry
before it closes up.
-Wait!
Just a thought here.
But what if we're just
getting in their way?
-That's right.
Like you say, I'm only a child.
-A-Un, hurry!
-[shouting]
-Damn.
Wasn't that a clever trick.
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
He could have hit me,
but he missed on purpose.
-Now I see.
Inuyasha's sword provides
the final link to his senses.
One that is easily broken!
[laughs] Without
his sword, I have
total control over Inuyasha.
-Inuyasha!
-Stand back.
You are interfering
with the fight.
[music playing]
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
Sesshomaru's playing right
into Naraku's hands.
That's it!
Tenseiga!
-Interesting.
Now that both your mind
and body are in demon form,
it makes you a bit
tougher than usual.
-Showing no mercy
to your own brother?
You must really hate Inuyasha.
-Hm!
I feel nothing towards him.
I've never consider that
half demon to be my brother!
-You are weak, Sesshomaru.
You fool!
Had you drawn
Bakusaiga, Inuyasha
would have been
obliterated in an instant.
But instead you chose
to draw Tenseiga,
a blade that cannot cut
through anything of this world.
You should have
know that as long
as I'm using Inuyasha's body
your Tenseiga is useless.
Now, prepare to die.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): I need to
get Tenseiga to him quickly!
SESSHOMARU
(VOICEOVER): You fool!
-Hang on, Inuyasha!
I'm bringing Tenseiga!
-Hah!
I'm afraid you're too late.
I, Magatshui, control every
corner of Inuyasha's heart.
Tenseiga's power can
no longer restore him.
He is lost to you now.
-Inuyasha, don't give in!
Inuyasha!
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): Huh?
That scent.
It's Kagome's blood.
-Please just let
me stay with you.
-If that's what you
want, then I promise
I'll protect you with my life.
Kagome!
-You just don't know
when to give up.
It's over!
There is nothing you can do now.
-Shut your-- shut your-- ah!
I said shut your mouth!
SESSHOMARU
(VOICEOVER): Inuyasha.
-No!
Impossible!
This cannot be happening!
-Kagome!
Are you there?
--I'm right up here!
-Kagome!
Tenseiga!
Give me Tenseiga!
-Right!
Inuyasha!
-Yes!
Tenseiga!
[shouts]
MAGATSHUI: Damn you!
-Kagome!
MAGATSHUI: Obey me!
Obey me!
-Kagome!
-Well, well, Magatshui.
What will you do now?
It appears the
half demon is more
difficult to control
than you thought.
-Do you want me to
leave Inuyasha's body?
Then why didn't you say
so in the first place?
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
However, if Magatshui
abandons Inuyasha's
body, he will try--
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): --to
take control of me next!
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER):
I'll have only one chance.
-Get away!
-I can't move!
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): He's
trying to move to Kagome.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): It hurts!
Inuyasha!
-Damn it!
I won't give in!
I refuse to let this beat me!
-It would've been a good
idea if you'd done it sooner,
but you were too late.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
You bastard!
You won't stop me
from protecting her!
Huh?
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Dragon-scaled Tessaiga?
-What?
I'm being forced out!
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
It's working.
Magatshui's being drawn out.
-What's wrong?
Have you given up hiding
in other people's bodies?
-What's happening!
I can neither return nor escape!
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): The source
of my demonic energy, my demon
vortex, has taken
hold of Magatshui.
-Ahhh!
-You couldn't have
picked a worse person
to try and possess.
-No!
I cannot lose to the demonic
energy of a half demon!
-Tenseiga!
It's over, Magatshui.
-Impossible!
[theme music]
MALE SPEAKER: Naraku
sets a trap using
a light which is returned
to the Shikon Jewel.
MALE SPEAKER: Once Sango's
Hiraikotsu destroys Rin,
the Shikon Jewel will again
be filled with darkness.
SANGO: Forgive me, Rin.
MIROKU: I don't care
if my Wind Tunnel
tears open as long as I'm able
to take Naraku and the Shikon
Jewel with me.
SANGO: No, Miroku!
That's just an illusion!
MALE SPEAKER: Next time on
"Inuyasha, The Final Act--
Naraku, The Trap Of Light."
MALE SPEAKER: Naraku will be
at the source of the light.