[theme music]
-Your injuries don't
seem to be bothering you.
-Nah.
Nothing hurts since
you saved my life.
-Hey, scrawny wolf boy.
-Huh?
-You're lucky to be alive.
-What's that?
-If you were smart,
you'd give us your shards
and go back your
wolf demon tribe.
-Huh.
You're starting to
sound like Kikyo.
I guess it shouldn't
come as a surprise to me,
though, seeing as
you two dated before.
-It's none of your
damn business.
I'll kill you.
SHIPPO (VOICEOVER): Having Koga
around really changes the mood.
I don't like it.
-If I can transfer the
miasma that's in him to me,
then I can use my
body to cleanse it.
-But won't that hurt you?
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER): Yes.
Her body is already been
consumed by Naraku's miasma.
But she'll remain silent.
-It's strange that
on the one hand,
you'd risk your life
to save him, yet--
-And yet, I'd lead your
brother, Kohaku, to his death.
Is that what you wanted to say?
If someone can be saved,
I'll try to save them.
That is all I can do.
MALE SPEAKER: "The
Mausoleum of Mount Azusa."
ONIGUMO: I see you've
finally returned, Naraku.
-I have, not by
choice, I assure you.
ONIGUMO: Naturally.
After all, your human
heart cared for Kikyo,
and you couldn't
have that, could you?
So you removed it and
sealed it away here, deep
within Mount Hakurei.
And yet, here you are.
Why is that, Naraku?
-Quite recently, I absorbed
Moryomaru and the Infant.
And as it was
happening, I suddenly
became aware that
Kohaku's jewel shard
was a very frightfully
pure light.
It occurred to me that if I
were to take it carelessly,
my Shikon Jewel would
instantly be purified,
and I myself along with it.
I believe that is
Kikyo's very intention.
[onigumo chuckling]
ONIGUMO: So now, you need the
heart you once so carelessly
discarded.
Perhaps you've realized that
the human heart isn't quite as
useless as you
believed it to be.
All those wicked thoughts,
despicable intentions,
pitiful attachments--
yes, Naraku.
All of those negative
human feelings for Kikyo
are what give the Shikon
Jewel its dark power.
-And those feelings would
allow me to kill her, right?
ONIGUMO: Indeed, they would.
But isn't that why you've
come to take me back?
NARAKU: Negative feelings.
That's right.
After all, what better weapon
is there to destroy her?
The negative feelings I harbor
are what connect Kikyo and I,
and you as well, InuYasha.
KIKYO: You're awake.
That's a good sign.
-Kikyo, have you saved me?
-I have, for now at least.
I was able to
cleanse the miasma,
but it left deep scars
within your body.
If you continue to
use your Wind Tunnel,
the scars from Naraku's
miasma will eventually
make their way to your heart.
When that happens, Miroku,
nothing can save you.
-I know.
I'm well aware of my
physical condition.
For that very reason,
I would prefer
that this remain between
us, if you don't mind.
-I understand.
MIROKU (VOICEOVER): Sango,
you have enough on your mind.
No matter what happens to me,
I won't regret what I did.
-Kikyo.
-The miasma has been
cleansed, but Miroku
will need to rest a
little while longer.
-So he's going to be OK?
-Yes.
-Kohaku.
So does this mean you're
leaving with Kikyo?
-Yes.
I'm sure we'll meet again soon.
INUYASHA: Kikyo,
look after the kid.
-I'll do what I can.
VOICEOVER: If I can find
a way to save him, I will.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
InuYasha must
be having trouble sleeping.
Is that a spiderweb?
-Kohaku, you must stay near me.
-OK.
KIKYO (VOICEOVER):
These spiderwebs
don't seem to have any
effect on the villagers.
Still, I know who's on the
other end of these threads,
and his intentions
are surely evil.
-Saki, we're going home.
-Kay, just one second, Mom.
-What is it, Saki?
What happened?
KIKYO: Stand back.
-Priestess.
KIKYO (VOICEOVER): Using
an innocent little girl--
Naraku will stop
at nothing to force
me to touch one of those webs.
-That way.
I can see webs
falling from the sky.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
This is Kikyo's scent.
-Um, yes.
It was a priestess
that saved my daughter.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): I knew it.
She was here.
-I see.
And what did the
priestess do next?
-It was strange.
She looked as if
she'd fallen ill.
And then she left.
-Hey, wait for us, InuYasha.
-I guess that priestess
must have been Kikyo.
-Boy, is that ever
cruel-- ditching Kagome
like that to go chase
after an old fling.
-Believe, Koga, you do
not want to go there.
-Maybe we can talk about
something else if that's OK.
-You must keep your distance
for me for the time being.
If you stay with me any
longer, your Shikon Jewel shard
will be defiled.
-What's happened
to you, Lady Kikyo?
KIKYO (VOICEOVER):
After all these years,
how dare you attempt to cloud
my mind with such visions.
INUYASHA: Kikyo!
-Stay back, InuYasha.
-Hang in there, Kikyo.
It's him.
-It's Naraku.
He knows of my plan.
He knows that I
intend to purify him
and the Shikon Jewel together.
-Save your energy.
Let's get you out of here.
Dammit.
The more I cut it, the
more entangled I get.
KAGOME: Over there!
-Uh, what is she shooting at?
-I guess those spiderwebs.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): InuYasha
and Kikyo are stuck inside.
-Is it Kagome who's
purifying those webs outside?
-Yeah.
I think Kagome can see them too.
KIKYO (VOICEOVER):
How can she see them?
Is this part of Naraku's plan?
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): He couldn't
purify the webs inside.
KIKYO: Don't touch the webs!
-Kagome!
A barrier.
[chuckling]
-Now, you are mine.
-Ha!
With this Shikon Jewel, finally,
I can become a full demon.
KAGOME: InuYasha!
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): I know this.
This was them 50 years ago.
My chest hurts.
It's as if something's
being transmitted
to me through the webs.
I think I can feel
Kikyo's sorrow.
But I feel something else, too.
It's a love that's as
deep as her sorrow.
It's a bond between two people
that can never be broken.
INUYASHA: Are you OK?
Kagome.
-They're gone.
-The three of us
are gathered here.
The webs must no
longer be needed.
-You saw.
I know what he wants.
-Your neck.
What happened?
-The moment I touched
his spiderwebs,
the miasma began to spread.
-That's OK.
I can heal that wound, right?
I did it once before.
-There is only one way.
You must shoot my
wound using this bow.
Only that can purify
Naraku's contamination.
-OK.
-The bow string--
you too have been
contaminated by
Naraku's spiderwebs.
-How can you be sure?
-Naraku set this trap for us.
To begin with, he
magnified my wound
so that I'd leave Kohaku behind.
He knew I would do that
rather than allow the miasma
from my wound to
defile his shard.
Next, he used me as a
decoy to bring InuYasha out
into the open.
Do you know why?
So he could plant negative
feelings in your heart--
the end result of the chain
of events he set into motion.
-But why would he
want to do that to me?
-You are the only one who
can cleanse Naraku's poison
from my body.
He couldn't have that.
That is why Naraku
showed you those visions
from 50 years ago.
He knew you couldn't purify me
with those negative feelings
in your heart.
-And now that Koga has lost the
protection of the wolf demon
tribe, Naraku can steal
his shards at any time.
I'm afraid there's
nothing we can do now.
-Don't just give up, Kikyo!
I can still save you.
There must be a way.
-Is everything
all right, Kagome?
-Yeah.
-Why's the pup have
such a long face?
Looks like he's about to cry.
-Kagome just busted
him trying to sneak off
for a secret meeting with Kikyo.
I'm sure it wasn't pretty.
-InuYasha, I think you
should stay here with Kikyo.
-You do that.
I can carry Kagome.
-Thank you, Koga.
-Kagome, look.
I--
-I just don't want to see
your face right now, OK?
Now that I think about it,
maybe I have been contaminated.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
No, I'm pretty sure
that's not the
contamination talking.
KIKYO: Head about 10
leagues east of here.
The bow can only be restored
using the bow string that
is kept in the mausoleum
on Mount Azusa.
But Kagome, if in your heart,
you do not truly desire
to save my life, it
will be impossible
for you to ever
reach the mausoleum.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): Why
is it that every time I
try to help Kikyo, I feel
like she's testing me?
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER):
Could something
have happened to Lady Kikyo?
BYAKUYA: I can see you.
-It's you.
-Run away.
-Yes, please run.
-Don't waste my time!
[flies buzzing]
-Your shikigami disappeared?
-Yes.
Please hurry.
We must find Kohaku.
-You'll never escape.
Up here.
This is pointless, Kohaku.
Remember, you belong to Naraku.
The venom in those
snakes is miasma.
I have to make sure I
sufficiently contaminate your
shard before I
take you to Naraku.
I see your methods
haven't changed.
Lord Sesshomaru, what
brings your here?
-Moryomaru's scent
has disappeared.
I presume he was
eaten by Naraku?
BYAKUYA: So you've come
to save Kohaku, have you?
It seems a bit out
of character for you.
-I noticed a foul smell,
and I came to get rid of it.
And here you are.
-Hate to disappoint.
But I must take my leave.
Perhaps next time, you'll be so
kind as to announce yourself.
-Kohaku.
SESSHOMARU: The
snakes are poisonous.
Don't touch him.
-OK, but what if you've
already been bitten?
-Please help me,
Lord Sesshobaru.
This beast doesn't
want to let go.
SHIPPO: Now, that's
a long stairway.
KAGOME: The Mausoleum
of Mount Azusa.
-Easy.
We'll be at the top in no time.
-Kohaku's scent
stops right here,
and looks to me like
Sesshomaru's crew took him
with them.
-I see.
-Kikyo, what's the matter?
Is the miasma spreading?
KIKYO (VOICEOVER): My body
will surely fail soon.
You are the only one
who can save me, Kagome.
-Dammit, what's going on?
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): Why
are we getting any closer?
Is it because I have doubts?
What is that?
Guys?
-A human.
KIKYO (VOICEOVER): It is
said that the spirit guardian
of Mount Azusa can appear
as a god or a demon.
Its appearance is
always a reflection
of the beholder's heart.
-Kikyo?
-How did we end up
back at the bottom,
and why isn't Kagome with us?
-No need to panic, Koga.
Mount Azusa is a
sacred mountain.
Kagome's disappearance can
only mean it has accepted her.
-Here.
Take it.
-Really?
-Thank you.
-Now, go.
If you truly desire
to save this woman,
you will be able to
take this bow back down
to the food of the mountain.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
It's the same
as when we were climbing up.
I can't seem to
reach the bottom.
-Kagome!
Where are you?
Kagome!
-Hey, I'm right over here.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): InuYasha.
Kikyo's here too.
-More spiderwebs?
-Hang in there, Kikyo.
I'm going after
Kagome now, all right?
-But I'm right here!
Can't you see me?
-Too late.
If Kagome hasn't returned,
it's because she's
been swallowed by Mount Azusa.
She was probably judged unfit.
They couldn't give
her the bow once she
was contaminated by spiderwebs.
I expected this.
After all, Kagome
feels she must compete
with me for your affections.
-You mean Kagome doesn't
actually want to save you?
Then what are we
supposed to do now?
-Hold on.
You're wrong.
That's not how I feel.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): Kikyo
could see me this whole time.
Why is she doing this?
-Something's happened to Kagome.
-What are you talking about?
KIKYO (VOICEOVER):
The spirit guardian
of Mount Azusa tests
people's hearts.
Kagome may be swayed by the
spirit guardian's illusions.
-I feel like my
arm's gonna tear off.
It's this bow.
It's so heavy.
KIKYO: Hand over the bow.
Now.
-Kikyo.
Go get InuYasha.
-This cliff is within a barrier
created by the spirit guardian.
A half-demon like
InuYasha cannot enter.
Now, give me the bow quickly.
-I can't.
It's so heavy, I
can't lift my arm.
-So it is true.
You desire my death,
just as I suspected.
-What about you?
Did you have any
intention of helping me?
SPIRIT GUARDIAN:
Throw away the bow.
-The spirit guardian
of Mount Azusa?
-Priestess, it is you who
desires this girl's death,
is it not?
For she is the woman who
stole your beloved man.
Tell me, what do you
think will happen?
Once she has the
bow, the priestess
will go to reclaim his
love, leaving you to die.
Of course, that won't happen
if you abandon her first.
It is a matter of survival.
-You are free to
abandon me if you wish.
I assure you, InuYasha cannot
see what is taking place here.
KOGA: This isn't right.
She's taken way too long.
I'm going.
INUYASHA: Cool it,
scrawny wolf boy.
KOGA: InuYasha.
-Please put me down here.
-Yeah.
Sure.
-I'll be waiting here for you.
Go find her.
-All right, then.
-Huh?
I thought you were gonna
to look after Kikyo.
-I'm going now.
I have to do this.
It's just that simple, OK?
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
I'm sorry, Kikyo.
[kikyo laughing]
KAGOME: What's so funny?
-Let me guess.
You were just thinking
that even if InuYasha
were to forgive you, you could
never forgive yourself, right?
Stop being so self-righteous!
You want everyone to think
you're so kind and dignified.
But I can see that your heart
is filled with envy and hatred.
Still, you play the
part, continuing
to pretend that you
actually pity me.
KAGOME: Pretend?
KIKYO: You claim to
feel sorry for me,
a poor dead woman
brought back to life.
But in truth, you grow impatient
because InuYasha cannot bring
closure to our relationship.
You can say you care and
offer me a helping hand,
but you're not fooling me.
I know what your
true feelings are.
-What are you talking about?
-Did you think I
wouldn't notice?
That I'd blindly cling
to your false kindness?
-Would you just cut it
out already, you idiot!
I let you talk for a minute,
and this is what I get?
Well, what gives you the right
to talk to me like that, huh?
If you and InuYasha have
such a great relationship,
then why don't you come
out in the open with it?
You're always looking
down on me, testing me,
but you're actually
scared of me, aren't you?
-Scared of you?
KAGOME: That's right.
The thing is, you and
InuYasha have a past together
that I could never compete with.
I can admit that.
But you know what?
Since we met, I've spent a
lot of time with InuYasha too,
and I bet I've seen
sides of InuYasha
that you have never seen.
(VOICEOVER): I know things about
InuYasha that Kikyo doesn't?
That means we're in
exactly the same position.
Understand?
I'm just saying I won't abandon
you out of fear or jealousy.
I don't need to.
(VOICEOVER) What's going on?
It was so heavy
just a moment ago.
-You are free to climb
up by yourself now.
Don't worry.
The priestess cannot harm you.
KAGOME: What is it, Kikyo?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Wait a minute.
It isn't her.
-My child, the priestess
was nothing more
than an illusion, one
that your heart created.
SPIRIT GUARDIAN:
The spiderwebs which
entangled you have
now been severed.
Use that bow to
save the priestess.
-Help.
Help me, InuYasha!
-Oh?
She has escaped?
She's free of my web.
-So what will you do, Naraku?
-Isn't it obvious?
I will take Kikyo's life
as I originally planned.
[theme music]
MALE SPEAKER: Naraku shows up
to destroy Kikyo and take away
Koga's Shikon Jewel shards.
KIKYO: Kagome, all
that remains is
for you to protect
Kohaku's light.
KAGOME: Kikyo, I thought you'd
be saved if I used the bow.
NARAKU: Kikyo is finished.
MALE SPEAKER: Next time,
on InuYasha, The Final Act,
"Among the Twinkling Stars."
KIKYO: At last, I have
become an ordinary woman.