[music playing]
[theme music]
-(THINKING) Huh?
What is this?
GIRL: I'm there!
-Me too!
-Oh yeah.
So is mine.
-Kagome, what about yours?
-Oh, (THINKING) that's right.
I almost forgot.
I made it through my exams.
-Isn't it awesome?
All of us passed.
-What about you, Kagome?
-Oh, um-- huh?
[nervous giggling]
It's not there.
No way!
I failed!
No!
[gasping] Huh?
I failed?
-What's wrong, Kagome?
Are you still in pain?
-But how'd I-- You
lost consciousness
after Magatsuhi glared at you.
Do you remember what happened?
-[gasp] (THINKING) That's right.
I remember now.
I suddenly felt weak.
[gasp] Kohaku, how is he, Sango?
-Well, he hasn't woken
up since it happened.
-I'm sure it's because
Magatsuhi defiled his shard.
Let me purify it.
-But I still don't
understand why Magatsuhi
was able to defile
Kohaku's shard.
MALE SPEAKER:
Magatsuhi originates
from the Shikon Jewel, which
contains a speck of light that
was planted there by Lady Kikyo.
When Naraku made contact
with Kohaku's shard,
that speck of light produced an
intense purifying illumination,
which seemed to
cause him great pain.
-Yeah, that's true.
Magatsuhi comes from the Jewel,
and was using Naraku's body.
When he touched
Kohaku's shard, it
should have had the same effect.
-I would presume that the speck
of light, the purification
spell planted by my sister is
only effective against Naraku.
-What do you mean by that?
The purification spell
was cast by my sister
in her final moments.
Naraku was her target.
It only makes sense that the
spell would apply to him,
and him alone.
-So it can't hurt Magatsuhi.
He's going to be quite
a challenging opponent.
It's a shame we couldn't finish
him off before he escaped.
-The next time
Magatsuhi shows up,
I'm going to give him
a taste of Tessaiga.
-How does it look?
Better?
-What's going on?
It's not working.
I can't purify it.
I--
-You, you can't?
-Kagome?
-I don't get it.
I could do this before.
-If you can't what will happen?
--[gasp] (THINKING)
Hold on a sec.
Did Magatsuhi do this to me?
-(THINKING) He did
something to Kagome's power.
The day of days.
-Honestly, how dare he bring
the mighty Lord Sesshomaru
to a lowly human
village like this?
-OK.
All done.
A scabbard for Bakusaiga.
-Hold on.
Please wait, Lord Sesshomaru.
Kohaku still hasn't
woken up yet.
If we wait a little longer I'm--
-Kohaku stays behind.
You too, you stay as well.
-Huh?
But, but why, Lord Sesshomaru?
-(THINKING) Kohaku I understand.
But he's leading Rin behind?
Then again--
-No, I want to go with you!
-You are acting like
a spoiled brat, Rin.
Lord Sesshomaru
is a born warrior.
He lives to fight.
It made no sense to
drag two kids around run
with him in the first place.
It is simply not practical.
-Jaken, you'll be
staying behind, too.
-What?
But you can't.
Why, Lord Sesshomaru?
No!
I want to go with you.
I won't let go.
-Hey, Sesshomaru,
what's all this about?
You're going after
Magatsuhi, aren't you?
-Magatsuhi is my prey now.
-You're weak, demon.
-(THINKING) Now that I
have learned his scent,
I shall hunt him
down, and kill him.
-[whimpering]
Whoa!
-What are you doing, Sesshomaru?
-Why not let him go?
-You know well that Magatsuhi
is not of this world.
Only Sesshomaru's Tenseiga is
capable of cutting him down.
-Please don't cry.
We'll just have to wait
for him like we always do,
Master Jaken.
-I'll be waiting.
-(THINKING) Please come
back soon, Lord Sesshomaru.
-InuYasha, Magatsuhi
must have been
the one who sealed
Kagome's powers.
It's the only explanation.
-Yeah, I know.
That means we'll have to destroy
Magatsuhi to undo the seal.
And I'm not very happy about
leaving the job to Sesshomaru
alone.
-Little demon, you're staying
behind as well, are you?
-It's Master Jaken!
-Will you please be
polite, little demon.
-That attitude is
bigger than he is.
-Huh!
Look who's talking, small fry.
KAGOME: Sorry, InuYasha.
-What for?
There's no reason
for you to apologize.
-I guess so.
But it's just frustrating.
I feel so useless.
-Don't worry about it.
We'll fix this.
Besides, I know it doesn't
seem like it right now.
But this is a good sign.
If Magatsuhi and Naraku
went to the trouble
of sealing your power, they
must be pretty scared of it.
-(THINKING) Am I really
a threat to them?
-Well, Naraku, it looks
like he isn't coming back.
-I'm not expecting
him to come back.
The body I lent him
has been destroyed.
-So you mean
Magatsuhi is no more.
-He cannot be killed.
Anyway, I have a good idea of
what Magatsuhi will do next.
In fact, I'm looking
forward to it.
-Look, I'm sorry.
I know it's a bad time to leave.
-It's OK.
We understand.
It's not your fault, Kagome.
-Sango's correct.
We'll be right here with Kohaku.
-Wait, Kagome.
You can't go home yet.
What's InuYasha doing?
He should be here.
-It's OK.
I spoke to InuYasha yesterday.
We said our goodbyes.
Well, I'll come back as soon
as my entrance exams are done.
-Kagome has gone back to
her homeland, has she?
-Uh, yeah.
Something about having
to face this weak demon
called entrance exams.
She's been talking
about it for a while.
-But is it safe for Kagome
to travel there by herself?
Couldn't you have gone with her?
-I'm sure she'll be fine.
It's actually a lot safer
there than it is here.
(THINKING) This battle
will only get worse.
If Kagome were to lose her life
somehow, just like Kikyo did,
I, I'd be-- it would
be hard to let her go.
But I'd rather she live safely
on the other side of the well
than to see that happen to her.
At least Kagome's family
is there on the other side.
She wouldn't be alone.
-Huh?
KAGOME'S MOTHER'S
VOICE: Dear Kagome, we
won a trip to a hot
spring in a local draw.
Sorry you couldn't make it.
-You mean nobody's here?
Oh well I guess I can't
really blame them.
They didn't know I was going
to come back, after all.
Huh?
I forgot school!
I'm so late.
I have to catch up on all
the schoolwork I've missed.
I don't have time to relax.
Huh?
It's Sunday?
[phone ringing]
WOMAN (ON PHONE): Hello.
-Hi, this is Kagome.
Um, is Yuka home.
WOMAN (ON PHONE): No.
She went out with
Eddie and Ayumi.
-Do you know if they're studying
at the library by any chance?
-Hmm.
I'm not sure.
Could you call her cell?
--[sigh] i don't even
have a cell phone.
I can't get a signal in
the feudal era, anyway.
I'll go to sleep.
Oh, I'm sleeping in a real bed.
[traffic noise]
-It's too noisy!
All right, time to eat.
So delicious.
I'm a genius in the kitchen.
Yeah, it's good.
[sigh] I want mom's cooking.
OK, time to hit the books.
After all, that's the
reason I came home.
(THINKING) I wonder what
InuYasha and the others
are doing right now?
Hang on!
What is InuYasha doing?
Usually he comes to bug me
right after I get back home.
Hmph.
I'm lonely, and after
I finally came home.
[sigh] Heavy.
Huh?
A blanket?
-So, you sleep well?
-InuYasha.
-What is it?
I didn't do anything
wrong, I swear.
-No, that's not it.
-Huh?
-I'm just so glad to see you.
That's all.
-Uh, OK.
So here.
Kaida said you should
hold onto this.
-The bow from Mount Azusa?
-Your spiritual power
might be sealed.
But it can still help
you clear your mind.
That will probably
help you in your battle
against entrance exam.
-Yeah.
I'm not sure how much
use it'll be, but thanks.
Huh?
-Well, guess I'll seeing you.
Later.
-Sit, boy.
-Why?
Nobody's here?
-Yeah.
-That's stupid.
Instead of sitting here
feeling sorry for yourself,
you should have just come back.
-Look, it's not that easy.
For one thing, I
have school tomorrow.
Plus, mom and everyone
might come home soon.
-Hmm.
Listen, Kagome.
-Huh?
-Do you, do you like
living here in this world?
-Yeah, of course I do.
This is where I was
born and raised.
And my family and
friends are here.
-Of course.
-What brought this on?
-Look, uh, how would you feel
about staying on this side
until the battle
with Naraku's over?
Hmm?
-Huh, there's no fever.
-I'm not delirious, OK?
I'm just looking out for you.
-[gasp] Oh.
I see.
Well, guess you don't
need me here anymore.
Next thing you know, you'll
be going to the hot springs
and stuff with Moroku and Sango.
-No, I'm not going
to any hot springs.
Huh?
Kagome, this is only
a fake, am I right?
-It's a lucky charm.
We sell them at our shrine.
Maybe Magatsuhi was able to
steal your spiritual power
because that was Kikyo's wish
back when she was still alive.
-Huh?
-Originally, the Shikon Jewel
was neither good nor evil.
It would reflect the
heart of its owner.
But within the Jewel, good and
evil are constantly at battle.
When Kikyo died after
we wounded each other,
she had no intention
of being reincarnated.
-I see.
All the feelings she had
for you were channeled
into this Shikon Jewel,
until they were reborn in me.
And then I ended up bringing
the Shikon Jewel back
into the feudal era.
So even if the seal on your
powers was Kikyo's wish,
it was only because she
didn't want to fight anymore.
The Jewel granted her her wish.
-That reminds me of something.
My grandpa once said,
when the person who
obtains the Jewel makes the
one and only correct wish,
then the Jewel will be purified,
and disappear from this world
forever.
Even if sealing my
powers was Kikyo's wish,
somehow it wasn't the
one and only correct
wish my grandpa
was talking about.
-Hmm.
-Not only that, I promised
Kikyo that I'd fight.
-Kagome, the rest is up to you.
-That's why I have to do this.
I have no choice.
InuYasha, do you
think I'll be stronger
once the seal has been removed?
-So you chose to fight?
Is that what you're
saying to me?
-I want to see this through.
But I know I can't stay with
you guys, unless I get stronger.
Anyway, I should say thanks.
It's sweet that
you'd worry about me.
-Uh, well, I, I guess so.
-Please just let
me stay with you.
-Uh, Kagome--
-[gasp]
-If that's what you
want, then I promise
I'll protect you with my life.
-InuYasha.
(THINKING) Is he
going to kiss me?
Yeah, I think he is.
KAGOME'S MOM: We're home!
-[gasp]
-Hey, Kagome.
When did you get back?
Uh, what are you guys doing?
-Well, we, uh, uh, I wish
I'd known you were coming.
Were you lonely, my dear?
-It's a shame you
couldn't have joined us.
-I know.
But I sure hope you didn't
hurry home on my account.
[nervous laugh] I didn't
realize that one day I
would have to choose between the
two worlds-- this one or his.
Exam ticket, pencil
case, and test guides.
OK.
(THINKING) It's finally here,
the day of high school entrance
exams.
Well, I'll see you later.
-You didn't forget
anything, right?
-We'll be praying
for your success.
-Yeah, just do your best, sis.
-(THINKING) Over
the past 10 days,
InuYasha never
came to visit once.
So I was able to focus
on studying for a change.
I'm as ready as I'll ever be.
I'm going to pass these exams.
-Oh, there she is.
-Kagome, we're over here.
-Hold on.
What is this?
Why isn't Kagome here?
-InuYasha, what
are you doing here?
-Isn't that kind of obvious.
Kagome told me to come back
and get her in 10 days.
So I'm here to take her back.
-Are you insane?
She's taking
entrance exams today.
-Huh?
-My boy, you may not be
able to understand this.
But Kagome's entire
life is riding on this.
Listen well.
Under no circumstances are you
allowed to bother Kagome today.
Wait a minute.
He's gone?
-He left a long time ago.
-He didn't hear a
single word you said.
RECORDING: The express
train with service to Tokyo
will be leaving from Platform
Four in three minutes.
-[panting]
-Whoa.
It's so crowded.
RECORDING: Until the train
has come to a complete stop.
-If we can just get
on this express train,
we'll make it there
with time to spare.
Let's go, girls.
INUYASHA: Hey, Kagome.
-What?
-And just where do you
think you're going, huh?
-InuYasha, why?
-We're going back.
You promised 10 days.
-Sit, boy.
-Hey wasn't that, uh--
-Your boyfriend.
-You're seeing things.
-Cosplay.
-Why is he barefoot.
-Hey, what are you
three looking at?
-Definitely cosplay.
-With a really bad temper.
-(THINKING) Yikes.
This is a total nightmare.
I mean, why would InuYasha
come for me today of all days?
Demons, makeup exams,
demons, extra classes,
demons-- looking back on all
that, I've gone through so much
just to make it to this point.
And so help me, I'm not about
to let InuYasha interfere today.
-Damn.
Stupid Kagome changing
her stupid attitude
all of a sudden.
-Please just let
me stay with you.
-If that's what you
want, then I promise
I'll protect you with my life.
I gave you my word, Kagome.
And I don't go back on my word.
You can run all you want.
But I won't let you get away.
ANNOUNCER (ON INTERCOM):
Shinjuku, Shinjuku,
this is Shinjuku.
-We're getting off.
-Excuse me.
-Uh, um, help!
Ah, my bag!
[screaming]
ANNOUNCER (ON INTERCOM):
Please stay back from the train
for your own safety!
I'm talking to you, miss.
-Kagome.
ANNOUNCER (ON INTERCOM): OK,
the next train is approaching.
Will you please stand back?
-My exam ticket!
-Kagome, find an attendant.
-Yeah, get an attendant
to report it, quick.
-Huh?
-Calm down.
-Kagome, your boyfriend's here.
-Huh?
-That's the train.
Hurry, InuYasha.
-All right.
-OK.
I knew we weren't seeing things.
That was her boyfriend
at the last station.
-Yeah.
Is it me, or does it
look like he's flying?
-Please catch it.
There's something more important
than my life inside that train.
-Someone stole it?
This world is pretty
dangerous, too, huh?
Finally.
It's about time you stopped.
Now take this!
-No!
No cutting.
Sit, boy.
Pardon me.
Coming through.
Excuse me!
I'm looking for my school bag.
There's a very important
exam ticket inside it.
-You'll pay for that, Kagome.
Huh?
-Come on.
It has to be in
this car somewhere.
-[sniffing]
-Where is it?
Whoa!
Stupid!
Why did you pull me-- [gasps]
-InuYasha.
-Is this it?
It had your scent.
-So is this the missing bag?
-Huh?
-Why are you crying?
-Thank you!
I am so, so glad you were here.
You completely saved my life.
-Yeah, well I'm glad you
finally figured that out.
-Applicants, the exam
is about to start.
-We're heading back
once you're done, right?
-Mhmm.
And thanks for getting me here.
Oh, my exam ticket.
Uh, exam ticket, exam ticket.
What?
It's not-- it's not here.
My exam ticket is gone!
It's over!
That's done.
-Huh?
-It's all over.
It was a short life.
-Oh, there she is.
Kagome!
[panting]
-Mother?
-Here, your exam ticket.
Go on.
I guess you must
have forgotten it.
I found it on your desk.
-[gasp] I don't believe it.
-I don't really get it.
But knock 'em dead, Kagome.
-Yeah!
(THINKING) What a morning.
I don't think I've ever
been that stressed.
It felt like a roller
coaster ride from heaven
to hell, and back
to heaven again.
-You've been dressed like
that the entire time?
-Of course.
-Let's hide those, shall we?
-Yeah, thank you?
KAGOME: (THINKING)
After all that,
I finally made it through my
high school entrance exams.
[music playing]
MALE SPEAKER: Byakuya leads
Sesshomaru on a wild chase,
while Miroku sucks in
poison, and collapses.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Magatsuhi
takes control of Kohaku's body,
and attempts to transport
the defiled shard to Naraku.
The shard forces Kohaku to
relive the dreadful sins
of his past, over
and over again.
Even so, you still have
to wake up, Kohaku.
MALE SPEAKER: Next
time on "InuYasha,
the Final Act: Kohaku's Shard."
MALE SPEAKER: Sister,
it isn't too late?