[music playing]
[theme music]
-Kikyo's magic has
no effect on me.
Now watch as the Shikon Jewel
is made whole once again.
-Kohaku!
-I'm here, sister.
-I see it!
There's a light inside
Kohaku's shard again.
-Impossible!
-Magatsuhi, you said Kikyo's
magic wouldn't work on you.
But it looks to me
like you were wrong.
-Yah!
Are you saying Kikyo's light
has moved into Kohaku's shard?
-Sister, wait.
Are you saying that it
really isn't too late for me?
-No.
It's never too late, Kohaku.
Kohaku!
-I'm being forced out!
-(THINKING) I won't let
you have this shard, never!
-Is Kikyo's light
giving Kohaku his power.
I can feel my grip
on it slipping.
Damn you!
-It's working.
-He's been forced out!
-(THINKING) My sister.
-There's still time.
It's not too late.
Kohaku!
INUYASHA: When the
Jewel is whole.
-Kohaku!
-Naraku!
(THINKING) Naraku's
inside that cloud.
-Kohaku!
-Sister, quick!
Cut the tentacle.
-Hiya!
-Kohaku, you all right?
-Yes.
-Now's our chance
to defeat Naraku.
Get Ready for this.
Meido Zangetsuha!
-(THINKING) The sky is clear.
Is Naraku dead?
No, I can sense the presence
of the defiled Shikon Jewel
all around us.
InuYasha, be careful.
Naraku's still alive.
He's around here somewhere.
-What?
Ah!
-Whoa.
-You tried.
But in the end,
it wasn't enough.
-How dare you!
-Lord Sesshomaru!
-Sesshomaru?
-Naraku's body, is it?
Bakusaiga!
-Kohaku!
-Sister.
-You're safe.
Are you hurt at all?
-Amazing.
-Looks like a body that's
been cut by Bakusaiga
can never be used again.
-It ends here, Magatsuhi.
Rather than face me, you chose
to use Byakuya of the Dream
so you could elude me.
Are you really that
fearful of Tenseiga?
-(THINKING) Tenseiga is the
only sword that can cut through
Magatsuhi.
And if Magatsuhi is destroyed,
my sealed spiritual power
will finally be released.
-Ha.
If you could destroy
me with Tenseiga,
you would have done it
with your first stroke.
-Oh, it's not that I
couldn't destroy you.
I merely chose not to.
-[growling]
-I wanted you to see my face.
That way, you know it was
me who was killing you.
-Ha!
-Tenseiga!
-[screaming]
Damn you!
Don't think that
this is the end.
I am indestructible.
And I will have my revenge!
-This isn't the end?
What does he mean?
-Heh, don't worry.
He's just bluffing.
-Why would he say that, Sango.
Does that mean Magatsuhi
isn't completely dead?
-(THINKING) It couldn't be.
-Rin, Rin, Rin, Rin.
Huh?
-It can't be.
-[gasp] What's happening?
-Please listen.
Before coming here, Magatsuhi
attacked the village.
In the battle,
both Miroku and Rin
were infected by his poison.
InuYasha, we should
go there, too.
I'm worried about them.
They're all alone.
-Right.
Let's go, Kagome.
-Sure.
-Naraku!
-[gasp]
-Kagome!
--[evil laugh] Kagome, it seems
your spiritual power has not
yet returned.
I have been hiding
behind a barrier.
But that you were unable
to sense my presence
surprised even me.
-Naraku, you bastard.
--[laughing] So what
are you waiting for?
Go ahead and start swinging.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm not planning to
kill her, not until I've
taken Kohaku's shard, that is.
-Huh?
-It won't happen!
-It's pointless.
All you've done it sever an
unnecessary tentacle, one
that can be sacrificed
at any time.
Just as InuYasha's Meido
Zangetsuhan Sesshomaru's
Bakusaiga did,
you've only destroyed
that which I did not need.
-(THINKING) Damn.
Right now Naraku believes that
I have no spiritual power.
But he's wrong.
I still have enough power
to find the Shikon Jewel.
It has to be somewhere
within his body.
If we aim directly for
it, we can defeat him.
Where?
His head, neck, his heart maybe?
InuYasha!
Sango!
The Jewel is in
Naraku's right shoulder.
-Huh, so you still had enough
spiritual power to see that.
-Naraku, you bastard!
Ah!
Damn it.
Another barrier, huh?
-What will you do,
InuYasha, protect
the shard or your
beloved Kagome?
If you don't hand over
Kohaku's shard, she will die.
-Damn.
Using such a dirty trick.
-It's not fair.
-No, not Kagome.
-(THINKING) If
InuYasha uses Tenseiga,
he'll end up
hurting Kagome, too.
But Hiraikotsu.
-Oh, it's my shard.
-Now, Sango.
His right shoulder.
-Huh?
(THINKING) The red Tenseiga.
I see.
If we time it just right--
-Naraku!
-And now!
I think we got him.
-[chuckling]
-Huh?
-Ah!
KOHAKU: Sister!
-[screaming]
-Sango!
Are you OK?
-I'm sorry.
Hiraikotsu is made to
shatter demonic energy.
Look at that.
-Is that Moryomaru's
armored shell?
-Ah, so you've noticed.
Have you ever heard
of the demon Meioju
He had the hardest shell of any
demon-- that is until Moryomaru
swallowed him, and made
his shell his armor.
It snapped Sesshomaru's
Tokijin with ease.
And I recall your Tenseiga
didn't fare much better.
When he ceased to be useful
to me, I consumed Moryomaru.
And now the Shikone
Jewel is protected
by that same impenetrable shell.
It was no accident that
you were able to attack me.
I allowed it.
I wanted you to see how
futile your efforts are.
Kohaku, the only way to
save Kagome's life now
is to sacrifice yourself,
and hand over the shard.
-I can't let Kagome die.
-Kohaku!
Don't do it.
He's lying.
He won't let her go.
-Well, well.
So you're awake already.
I'm impressed.
-(THINKING) It may
be sealed right now.
But Kagome's spiritual power
is the thing Naraku fears most.
We have to use that
to our advantage.
-(THINKING) There must be
some way to save Kagome.
Huh?
That light, it's one
of the arrows Kagome
dropped when she was attacked.
Why is it shining?
That's right.
The one speck of light from Lady
Kikyo is still within my shard.
-Is your life that
dear to you, Kohaku,
that you're willing
to sacrifice Kagome?
-Watch out Kohaku!
Don't worry.
I'll save Kagome.
-It's hopeless.
-Huh?
It feels like I'm
being sucked in!
InuYasha!
-Hang on.
I'm coming for you!
-It seems you still
don't understand.
It is I who holds the advantage.
KOHAKU: Give me
your word, Naraku.
-Huh?
-Kohaku, run away!
What do you think you're doing?
-Promise me that you'll
return Kagome unharmed
if I give you my shard.
-Hmm.
You have my word, Kohaku.
-No, Kohaku.
You can't do this.
-He's lying to you.
Don't do it.
Naraku would never
let me go free.
You know that.
Besides, the Shikon Jewel
shard sustains your life.
If you lose it,
you're going to die.
-It's no matter.
His life was forfeit
to begin with.
He has nothing to lose.
-Yes, my life was forfeit.
-Snap out of it, Kohaku.
-Don't be fooled
by Naraku's lies.
-Sister, please
let me handle this.
-Kohaku?
-That's right, Kohaku.
The day you murdered
your father and comrades
with your own hands,
on that day you died,
both in body and in spirit.
-It's true.
There have been
many times when I
felt it would've been better
if I had simply died back then.
-Kohaku.
-(THINKING) For a long time, I
spent every day thinking about
dying.
But things have changed.
I'm different now.
My sister, InuYasha,
and the others
have given me the strength
to life and fight on.
I'm going to save Kagome,
whatever it takes.
I have Lady Kikyo's
light, and Kagome's arrow.
The two are connected
through my hand!
Take this, Naraku!
Naraku!
I will defeat you.
I will not die!
-Damn you.
-The shell that Tessaiga and
Hiraikotsu couldn't destroy.
-It's falling apart.
-(THINKING) Amazing.
Light is flowing from the arrow.
But how?
It has to be coming
from Kohaku's shard.
[gasp] This is Kikyo's light.
-(THINKING) If I don't
break free from Kohaku soon,
I'll be consumed by
this purifying light.
-Kohaku!
-InuYasha!
-(THINKING) I'm going
to crush Naraku's skull!
Adamant Barrage!
-[screaming]
-Kagome!
Kagome, are you OK?
-Yeah.
It looks like Naraku
escaped into the clouds.
-Damn coward.
-Kohaku!
-Huh?
There you are, sister.
-Kohaku, you did well.
I'm so proud of you.
-To be honest with you,
sister, I still have doubts.
After what I did, do
I deserve to be alive?
-You do.
From this day on, you
have to live, Kohaku.
You can overcome your past.
-Miroku, are you sure you're
ready to be up and about?
-Yes.
Sorry to worry you
like that, Shippo.
-Miroku, I just felt an
ominous presence exit
your body, the likes of
which I've never known.
I can't be sure.
But that may have been the part
of Magatsuhi that you absorbed.
-That could very well be it.
I can't tell you how
much better I feel.
-Oh!
Maybe it means InuYasha and
the others defeated Magatsuhi.
-I certainly hope so.
-Honestly, don't make
me worry like that.
-I'm sorry, Master Jaken.
I'm fine now.
-Let me remind you, my
life is also at stake here.
Needless to say,
if anything were
to happen to you while
Lord Sesshomaru was
gone I'd be-- huh?
Hey!
Are you even listening to me?
Huh?
Wha-- hey!
Where are you going?
Come back!
Huh?
Rin!
-Where's Naraku?
-I don't know how.
But Kohaku's strike
really did some damage.
-Yeah, thank you, Kohaku.
You saved my life.
-I'm glad.
-Everything's OK now?
I mean, you'll be staying
with us from now on, right?
-Yes, I will, sister.
(THINKING) I know my
sins haven't been erased.
But I'm done running away.
From now on, I'll face them.
From now on, I'll live!
-[gasp]
-Huh?
-Huh? (THINKING)
That's Kohaku's shard.
-Kohaku!
Oh no!
Kohaku!
(THINKING) It's gone, the shard
that was sustaining his life,
it's gone.
-(THINKING) Kohaku!
This can't be happening.
-Why now?
Why did this have to happen now?
-Sister, wait.
Are you saying that it
really isn't too late for me?
-[crying] No!
[weeping]
NARAKU: At last, the brightness
of evil rejoin as one.
Kikyo's light has died out.
And Kohaku's shard
is fully defiled.
Finally, the Shikon
Jewel is complete.
Nothing shall stand in my way!
-She what?
-Rin was abducted?
-That's right, Miroku It
was the demonic presence
that came from your body.
It enveloped her,
and she was gone.
MIROKU: That means
it was Magatsuhi.
-So Magatsuhi is the one
responsible for taking her.
-Jaken, how could
you let that happen.
You were supposed
to be watching her.
-I know that!
(THINKING) What do I do?
Run away?
When he returns to
find Rin missing,
Lord Sesshomaru
will surely kill me.
SESSHOMARU: So.
-Ah!
SESSHOMARU: Magatsuhi survived.
-Oh no!
Lord Sesshomaru.
-As I expected.
-Expected?
Sesshomaru, what exactly did you
mean when you said he survived?
-Wait.
Are you suggesting that
Magatsuhi true form
was hiding in the
monk all this time?
-He could have at least answered
the question before flying off.
Not exactly Mr.
Personality, is he?
-(THINKING) He left without
so much as glancing at me.
Is Rin in that much
danger that he didn't even
have time to kill me?
-(THINKING) Magatsuhi would
have taken Rin to Naraku,
and for one purpose only-- to
seal the powers of Tenseiga
and Bakusaiga.
-[weeping]
--[roaring] Where's
Naraku hiding?
Find him for me, Kagome!
-(THINKING) I see it, Naraku's
blackened Shikon Jewel.
I'll use my sacred arrow.
It may be powerless right
now, but it can still
show InuYasha the way.
-Over there?
Meido Zangetsuha!
NARAKU: [laughing] You
let your guard down.
-Huh?
NARAKU: InuYasha, perhaps now
you realize how weak you are.
Despite your efforts, you
couldn't save your dear Kohaku.
But you must be
used to it by now?
You didn't fare much better
when you tried to save Kikyo.
That's right.
Kikyo's light has died.
-[gasp]
KOHAKU: And as for
Kohaku's shard,
it has now been fully defiled.
-(THINKING) It's true.
Kikyo's speck of light in the
Shikon Jewel has disappeared.
-[growling] Damn it!
Damn it!
-InuYasha.
-[weeping]
-(THINKING) I'm sorry, Sango.
I'm sorry, Kohaku.
[gasp]
-What is this?
-Huh?
-[gasp]
-Kohaku?
-S-sister.
-When Naraku took it, Kikyo's
light must have left the shard,
and stayed inside Kohaku.
-Kikyo's light?
KAGOME: Kikyo saved him.
In the end, and she
must have decided
it was more important
to save Kohaku's life,
than to destroy Naraku.
-Kohaku, I'm so glad.
-Me too, sister.
KAGOME: (THINKING) The
fight against Naraku
has been left to us.
It's time to finish it!
[music playing]
SHIPPO: Why are you leaving
me behind, InuYasha?
INUYASHA: Look, if
we don't come back,
you'll have to take over for us.
You understand, Shippo?
KAGOME: This is
the final battle.
Naraku transforms
into a giant spider,
and Sesshomaru charges
in without hesitation.
Now it's our turn.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"InuYasha, The Final Act:
Inside Naraku."
KAGOME: Rin's inside there.
Come on InuYasha!
INUYASHA: Time to
settle this, Naraku.
I'm going to defeat you, and
end this once and for all.