[music playing]
[theme music]
KAGOME'S MOM: Hello,
Higurashi residence.
Oh, Kagome, how
did your test go?
That's good to hear.
-Anyway, mom, have you
started cooking dinner yet?
Good.
Because I want to have a fest.
-Sure.
But can do the shopping, dear?
-Ah, excellent.
My bonsai make me
grateful to be alive.
Gazing at the magnificent
foliage soothes the soul.
Huh?
-Stupid Kagome still
hasn't come back.
I guess I'll just have
to go and get her.
Where'd she go?
[sniffing] [gagging]
-Hurt my bonsai,
you suffer my wrath.
-[gagging] Stop, please.
-Hey, I'm home.
What are you two doing?
If you're wondering where
sis is, she's shopping.
-She's shopping?
-Yep, she's done with exams,
so we're having a huge dinner.
-Hah, dinner?
I think I can help with that.
-Uh, hey, what's the hurry?
-I might have bought
too much food.
Oh well.
InuYasha will be with
us tonight anyway.
So--
-Delicious.
This meal is so good.
I don't think I've ever enjoyed
such a peaceful and utterly
fulfilling meal in all my life.
-That's so nice.
You just relax, and keep
on eating, all right?
-This is pure joy.
I'm so happy.
And the food is so good!
-[giggling] Oh, that InuYahsa.
I swear, he can be
so cute sometimes.
Hi, mom.
Sorry I'm late-- uh, pigeons?
-Hey, Kagome.
I heard we're having
a feast tonight.
So I got some
ingredients for you.
-(THINKING) Pigeons?
[cooing]
-Am I supposed to clean them?
-Uh, aren't those koi?
-Yeah, I caught them.
-From someone's pond, right?
Go put them back!
-Are you kidding me?
Those things weren't
easy to catch, you know.
-Take them back.
INUYASHA: (WHIMPERING) OK.
-[screaming]
-What's the matter, mom?
-Cockroach!
KAGOME: Cockroach?
-Stand aside.
I shall slay the vile creature.
Huh?
-Let me handle this.
-Huh?
INUYASHA: Wind star!
Oops.
NARRATOR: Kohaku's Shard.
-Shippo, I see you're
looking down the well again.
Kagome is supposed
to come back today.
She said so.
-Well, I'll come back as soon
as my entrance exams are done.
-InuYasha went to get her.
But he hasn't come back.
-Ah, yes.
That's right.
(THINKING) Sadly, Kagome's
power of purification
will still be sealed.
And Kohaku will
remain unconscious
with his shard defiled.
-I can't believe he
can continue to sleep
without eating or
drinking anything.
-That's OK.
Sleeping is good for children.
It helps them grow.
You probably didn't get
enough sleep, Master Jaken.
-Huh?
What is that supposed to mean?
-Well, maybe that's
why you didn't grow.
-Look here.
I'll have you know I
am a fully grown demon.
-(THINKING) Until Sesshomaru
destroys Magatsuhi,
Kohaku will not wake up.
It's hard to see him like this.
But it's been so long since we
spent this much time together.
How ironic.
Even though he's
unconscious, just the fact
that he's here with me
put my mind at ease.
-Wow.
You know how to
write, good monk?
-Amazing.
-So what's that word mean?
-This is how you write daughter.
-How about that one?
-That's princess.
And this is elder sister.
Younger sister is this.
And bride is written like this.
-How come all your
words are about girls?
-Hmm?
-What's that?
-It's like the sun
just disappeared.
-Please do something.
-Everybody get inside
the house right now.
(THINKING) Are these Naraku's
minions, or Magatsuhi's?
-(THINKING) Magatsuhi's
scent is near.
-Well, well, you came
flying all this way
after catching Magatsuhi's sent?
To the great Lord Sesshomaru
has a sharp nose indeed.
-Byakuha of the dreams.
-Hmm.
A left arm, I thought
you didn't have one.
Did it grow back?
-This has nothing
to do with you.
Be gone.
-I see your manners haven't
improved since last time.
You're only interested
in this one, I suppose.
-Magatsuhi.
Tenseiga!
It didn't work.
-Swing that sword all
you want, Sesshomaru.
That Magatsuhi is merely
an illusion I've created.
By now the real one is right
back where you started.
[screaming]
KAEDE: What an ominous
demonic presence.
-I want to help
Kohaku and the others.
-Not yet, Shippo.
First, you'll take the
villagers to a safe place.
-But I--
-Just do as I say.
We don't have much time.
-Wind tunnel.
-Miroku, no!
(THINKING) I can't
let him do this.
If he overuses his wind tunnel,
his wound will open again.
Here I come!
Let me handle the rest.
-Huh?
(THINKING) The shadows
haven't disappeared.
-Miroku?
-Damn it.
These demons are
only a distraction.
Their true objective is Kohaku.
-Master Jaken.
-Huh?
-There's a really weird shadow.
-Hmm?
[evil cackle]
-What?
-Oh no!
-You've shown yourself.
-Kohaku!
Did Magatsuhi take
over his body?
-This boy possesses within
him the final shard.
It will complete
the Shikon Jewel.
-Kohaku.
Give Kohaku back.
-Worry not.
I shall return his body
when I'm finished with it.
That is, I shall
return his corpse.
Now that I've taken control
of his body, it's clear to me
that the boy's life
is being sustained
by the power of the shard.
-He intends to take
Kohaku to Naraku
with the Jewel shard
still inside him.
-I won't let you
take him anywhere.
-Ha!
-[gasps]
-Do you hear something?
-Kohaku!
-Wait, Magatsuhi.
-Will you pull the boy to his
death with your wind tunnel?
-You are the only one
who will be pulled in.
Wind tunnel!
-Ah!
-I think he got him.
-What were you
hoping to achieve?
[evil cackle] As long as this
defiled Jewel shard is here,
my power is infinite.
Did you honestly believe
that you could absorb me?
However, monk, you have taken
in something that was never
meant for humans-- the
poison of evil spirits.
-Why'd you do that?
-Are you ready?
It's time for you
to die, sister.
And you shall die by my hand.
-Magatsuhi, I know it's you!
Huh?
Ah!
-Kohaku, stop that!
-Come back, Rin!
That isn't Kohaku anymore.
Magatsuhi has possessed
the boy's body.
-Ah!
-Rin!
-Way to go.
That dinner was a disaster.
And don't even get me
started on the kitchen wall.
-I get it.
I said I was sorry.
What more do you want from me?
-Huh?
Something's not right here.
-I smell blood and poison
from Kaede's house.
-Huh?
Hurry, InuYasha.
Kaede's house, it's
been destroyed.
What's going on?
-Where is everyone?
Huh?
-[gasp]
-Miroku!
Sango!
-Sango, what happened to you?
-Kohaku.
Please go after him.
-Hey, hang in there.
-I'm sorry, InuYasha.
I don't have much time.
-Miroku, what happened?
[gasp] (THINKING) The
scar from the miasma
has reached his chest.
-Because of the master
of potions' medicine,
I didn't feel it happening
while I was fighting.
So I ended up overdoing it.
[wind howling]
-Huh?
What's that sound?
-Miroku, is that
your wind tunnel?
-Huh?
-(THINKING) Will
the miasma kill me,
or will my wind tunnel
tear me apart first?
Either way, I don't
have much time left.
INUYASHA: You idiot.
That's why I warned you.
-Listen to me, InuYasha, we
don't have time for this right
now.
Go after Kohaku.
-Damn.
Both of you, sit tight
until we get back.
You got that?
Let's go, Kagome.
-Right.
(THINKING) Miroku!
-(THINKING) that's odd.
This scent is unmistakable.
It must be him.
Now I understand.
How foolish of me.
-Whoa.
-So that's where the
scent was coming from.
-Yes, of piece of Magatsuhi's
flesh that you sliced off.
It carries a fraction
of the soul that
couldn't escape in time, more
than enough to summon you
from a great distance.
Unfortunately, it took
you too long to notice.
My condolences.
But, since you're
here, I figure why not
have you amuse me
a while longer?
-You underestimate me, Byakuya.
Do you honestly believe you can
impede me with demons as weak
as these?
-Well, that is why I
gathered a thousand of them.
-[shouts]
-What?
All of them at once?
-InuYasha, please hurry.
Magatsuhi's influence has
left Kohaku's shard darker
than I've ever felt it before.
I just hope I can
still purify it.
-This is terrible.
-We must rebuild Lady
Kaede's house at once.
-Ah.
SHIPPO: Sango?
-Yes, Shippo?
-Aren't those wounds painful?
-Don't worry.
I'm fine.
-But Sango, Miroku's
not doing so well.
Shouldn't you stay
here with him?
-Naraku is certain
to be there to take
Kohaku's shard from him.
If I can somehow defeat Naraku,
the curse will be lifted.
And Miroku's wind
tunnel will disappear.
-Sango.
-Settling things
once and for all
is the only way to fix
this situation now.
-Hey, why are we stuck in
this musty storage shed.
-It'll do.
Don't complain, little demon.
[wind howling]
-(THINKING) Rin still isn't
showing any signs of waking up.
Wait.
If Lord Sesshomaru were
to find out about this,
my life will most
surely be over.
Ah!
He's here!
Oh, please forgive
me, Lord Sesshomaru.
How could I let this happen?
I'm so-- it's only
the demon slayer.
Don't scare me like that.
-How is he?
-He's still asleep, but
doesn't appear to be in pain.
SAIGO: So he was
unable to feel pain.
He only took the master
potions' medicine
so he'd be able to
fight by my side.
If only he'd felt it, he never
would have pushed himself
to the point where his
wind tunnel would tear.
Lady Kaede?
-Hmm?
-If you wouldn't mind, could
you give us a moment alone?
-Really, I still don't
understand why all of us
had to be chased out.
-Rin must have been infected
by Magatsuhi's poison.
I shall make her an infusion
to ward off evil spirits.
-(THINKING) Miroku, you've
always been willing to risk
your life for Kohaku and me.
Miroku.
Oh, Miroku.
Please don't die.
-Look at that cloud.
-It's Naraku.
-He's about to take
Kohaku's shard.
-I won't let that happen.
Adamant barrage!
Kohaku!
-So you've come back to
take the Jewel shard.
Get any closer, and I shall
tear this boy's body apart,
limb from limb.
I am immaterial.
I won't hurt me.
This boy's body is nothing more
than a vessel for the shard.
-(THINKING) The defiled
shard, I have to purify it.
[gasp]
-Foolish girl.
It's hopeless.
Don't tell me you've
already forgotten
that I sealed your
spiritual power.
-Even the sacred
arrow doesn't work.
-Kikyo's magic has
no effect on me.
-Now watch as the Shikon Jewel
is made whole once again.
-Kohaku, snap out of it!
-Snap out of it, you say?
Ha.
Don't you know what'll
happen when he does?
-What's that?
-Let's just say, if you could
see what the blackened Shikone
Jewel shard was showing Kohaku
right now, you'd understand.
--[panting] F-father,
I'm really scared.
Oh, sister, please
help me, sister.
SANGO: Kohaku!
-Sister!
-Kohaku!
Why, Kohaku?
-Did I do this?
I killed father, and everyone?
MAGATSUHI: All of
Kohaku's dreadful sins,
the power of the
shard is forcing
him to relive the day he
killed his father and clan,
over and over again.
-No way.
-So this entire time?
-All this time.
If Kohaku's forced to wake up
now to the reality of his past,
it would break his very soul.
No.
I'd say that his soul
has already been broken.
SAIGO: Even so, you still
have to wake up, Kohaku.
-Huh?
-Wake up, Kohaku!
-What a cruel sister you are.
If I wake up, I'll die.
You should know that.
-You have to fight back, Kohaku.
-Your words are meaningless now.
The damage is done.
-Oh no.
What have I done?
[crying] I need help.
Somebody, please help me.
Huh?
Sister.
I'm so glad.
She's OK after all.
No.
She's not OK!
I hurt her again!
Miroku tried to save me,
and he was hurt, too.
Sister, Miroku.
-Please help me, Kohaku.
-[gasp]
-Help this man.
And help me.
I beg you.
-Help?
Me?
You think I can help?
-Don't worry.
You can do it.
-Sister, I--
-You are my little
brother, after all.
-Uh!
-Kohaku!
-I'm here, sister.
-Do you recognize me?
Kohaku?
-Yes, I recognize you.
-He woke up!
How?
-I see it.
There's a light inside
Kohaku's shard again.
-Impossible!
-Magatsuhi, you said Kikyo's
magic wouldn't work on you.
But it looks to me
like you were wrong.
-Yah!
Are you saying Kikyo's light
has moved into Kohaku's shard?
-(THINKING) That's right,
the soul collector.
Lady Kikyo was the one that
rescued me from the past.
Sister, wait.
Are you saying that it
really isn't too late for me?
-No.
It's never too late, Kohaku.
Magatsuhi, so, are
you ready to die?
-How amusing.
You intend to jump, is that it?
Do you think I'll get
scared, and escape your body?
It's futile!
To be sure, as a vessel,
you will be of no use to me.
But rest assured, I will
still control the flesh
around this shard.
-I wouldn't be so sure.
Because you won't be
able to escape in time.
InuYasha and my sister
will take the shard
before you get the chance.
I swear it will never
be yours, Magatsuhi.
-Kohaku!
-Damn it.
What the hell's
wrong with this kid?
-I'm being forced out!
-(THINKING) I won't let
you have this shard, never!
-It's Kikyo's light
giving Kohaku his power.
I can feel my grip
on him slipping.
Damn you!
-It's working!
-He's been forced out.
-My sister.
-There's still time.
It's not too late.
Kohaku!
[music playing]
FEMALE SPEAKER: Sesshomaru
finally corners Magatsuhi.
Naraku appears in pursuit of
the final Shikon Jewel shard,
while Kohaku does
his best to resist.
KOHAKU: Naraku, I
will defeat you.
I will not die.
FEMALE SPEAKER: This
can't be happening.
The shard that was sustaining
his life, it's gone!
MALE SPEAKER: Next
time on "InuYasha,
The Final Act: When
the Jewel is Whole."
FEMALE SPEAKER: I can see it,
Naraku's blackened Shikone
Jewel.