[theme music]
KANNA: As I pass through
the lengthy struggle of life
in this fleeting world, I cannot
help but long for the midnight
moon I once saw.
-Do not let him escape, Kagura.
[roar]
KAGURA: (VOICEOVER)
He's consuming them.
-Hey, Goryomaru.
What exactly are you?
And why has Naraku
imprisoned you in here?
HAKUDOSHI: If you truly
wish to know the answer
to your questions,
then release him.
-Hakudoshi.
-You too afraid of
Naraku to follow through.
-I suppose you have no
fear of betraying Naraku.
GORYOMARU: Enough of this.
The time has come for you
to make a choice, Kagura.
Will you die as a
slave to Naraku,
or will you escape with
me and have your freedom?
-What?
Freedom?
-Yes.
Freedoom.
If you truly desire
liberation from Naraku,
then you must destroy him.
KAGURA: (VOICEOVER)
Originally, these two
came from Naraku's heart, which
he removed at Mount Hakurei.
Afterwards, that strane
monk split it in two,
leaving Hakudoshi
and the infant.
-I assure you, when
the time comes,
I will return your heart to
you before I obliterate Naraku.
-Huh.
And?
What do you expect me to do once
Goryomaru has been released?
-We still lack the necessary
power to overcome him.
And there's only
way to attain it.
-Now I see.
You need jewel shards.
Right?
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER)
Naraku's Heart.
-Close enough for you, Miroku?
-Wow.
That's fantastic.
You look like me
from every angle.
Now, you've just got to hang
around Sango in that form,
all right?
-Seriously?
You mean the whole time
Inuyasha's at Kagome's house?
-Yes.
I'm going to spread
my wings for a bit.
Ah!
-He threatened me
with his Wind Tunnel!
-So typical.
-(VOICEOVER) Aw, I don't get it.
I just don't get it.
I don't even know what
I'm not getting anymore.
-She's taking
another make-up exam?
-Yeah.
She's got tons of
catching up to do.
-I just hope she's ready
for entrance exams.
Huh?
Hey.
-Whoa.
What are you doing here?
-(VOICEOVER) OK.
You know you know this.
I'm positive this question's
from the study guide.
Got it.
I can do this!
-So, did you come
to pick up Kagome?
-That's so sweet.
-Yeah.
I know.
-(VOICEOVER) Focus.
I'm so close to solving this!
Huh?
-I think I just
heard something snap.
-That's the sound of
broken concentration.
-Yeah, I've heard that before.
-Sit, boy!
-Ah!
Kagome, what the
hell was that for?
-I specifically told
you to wait at home!
-I couldn't just sit
around there all day.
-I was trying my best to get out
of here as quickly as possible.
But then you-- you
distracted me and made
me forget all the
equations that I
was getting very
close to remembering.
-Glad I'm not in
his place right now.
-No kidding.
Look how she uses
fear to control him.
-You didn't get one right.
You'll be lucky if can find
a school that will take you.
GIRL: Are you OK, Kagome?
[sigh]
-Heh.
I bet you're glad I came to
get you at school now, huh?
-They're so lovey-dovey.
-We'll be going now.
You two have fun.
-See ya.
-Uh-- wait a sec.
Oh, well.
I'm home!
MRS. HIGURASHI:
Welcome home, Kagome.
Oh.
-You just got home,
and you're leaving?
-I see you're restless as usual.
-It won't get in
the way of studying.
I promise.
-Let's go, Kagome.
-Bye.
-Goodbye, sweetheart.
Take care of yourself.
-Hey, Kagome, you want me
to take care of these school
and entrance exam
things for you?
Just show me where to find 'em.
-This isn't something
you can take care of.
-Yeah, right.
You're saying I can't
take a couple of demons
with stupid names like that?
That's like saying I can't
take a weakling like Jaken.
-Ah-choo!
-Master Jaken, are you sick?
-No, but I have the
overwhelming sensation
that someone is
talking about me.
SESSHOMARU: Jaken.
-Huh?
-Have there been any
changes in the crystal?
-Not at all.
I can still sense
a demonic aura,
which can only mean that
we're not near the Fuyoheki
that Naraku uses to
conceal his heart.
And of course, that begs
the obvious question--
[singing]
-If it's not around here,
then where could it be?
RIN: (SINGING) Now
he's been left behind.
-Huh?
Hey, aren't you
forgetting someone?
-Oh!
Hang on.
-Huh?
-I knew I brought too many.
I should have left some at home.
INUYASHA: Just what
we need right now.
-Feel free give me a hand.
Huh?
Saimyosho!
-Naraku!
-What a nice surprise.
You dropped out of
sight for so long,
I was beginning to
worry about you.
-Hakudoshi!
[scream]
-Kagome!
-The Shikon jewel shard!
-Hold on, Kagome!
-Remember not to use
your Wind Tunnel, Miroku.
The Saimyosho will poison you.
-Not to mention you'll
suck in the jewel shard.
-Now that I have
the jewel shard,
I no longer have any
business with you.
-You won't get away that easy.
Wind Scar!
-Farewell.
-Damn!
He got away.
-It's OK.
I can sense the
Shikon jewel shard.
We'll find him.
[heavy breathing]
BOY: Wait up, Koga!
-Not a chance!
-But why are you
in such a hurry?
-Because I smell something
real shady around here.
-At last, the Shikon
jewel shards have arrived.
[scream]
[roar]
MALE VOICE: Kohaku, go
and hunt strong demons.
-Huh?
That must be the
demon's true form.
Huh?
Gotcha!
-What is it, Taichi?
Huh?
-Father--
-You OK?
That's a pretty nasty cut.
Does it still hurt?
-No.
It feels a lot better.
-That should do it.
-Thank you.
Huh?
Oh!
(VOICEOVER) He's been
possessed by the demon.
-Taichi!
-No!
Stay back!
Father-- Stop!
-My son-- it's me!
-He can't hear you now.
That thing's controlling him.
-Taichi!
-Don't worry, I'll
bring him back to you.
I won't let this kid
end up like I did.
I won't allow it to happen!
-Huh?
KAGURA: Dance of Blades!
Hello.
-Kagura.
-I've learned the location
of Naraku's heart.
-Really?
You did?
-Yes.
However, Kohaku, you stand
no chance against it.
Because you will die here!
-Whoa!
-Nicely done!
-He got it?
KOGA: (VOICEOVER) Damn!
He just keeps regenerating, no
matter how many times I attack.
Just like Naraku.
Wait.
That's it.
Now I know what smelled shady.
You're one Naraku's
allies, aren't you?
-And so what if I am?
-I'll kill you!
This is for my pack, bastard!
[laughter]
-No, I'll kill you, and
take your jewel shards.
What?
You and I aren't finished.
-You're damn right
we're not finished!
-Was that the sacred arrow?
-You mean Miss Kagome?
-Not her.
-I can't believe how
much spiritual power
I lost with just one shot.
But that Moryomaru demon
appears to be a lot different
than the last time I saw it.
It's as though he's
acquired a soul.
-If you know where
Naraku's heart is,
then you've got to tell me!
-I'll need your Shikon
jewel shard first, boy!
You'll die once I
take your shard.
If you cooperate, I
promise to make it quick.
There's nowhere to run.
Are you prepared to die?
-I've been prepared to
die for a long time now,
but I have no intention
of dying here.
If you need a
shard so badly, you
can take me there and
present me as an offering.
Then at least I can plunge
my blade into Naraku's heart,
even if it costs me my life.
Isn't that the
reason you gave me
this crystal in the
first place, Kagura?
I may have been under Naraku's
control at the time-- Father!
But it was still me who
killed my father and comrades.
-That way!
Don't worry.
I can tell Hakudoshi
isn't far off.
Huh?
-What is it?
-I just sensed another
Shikon jewel shard.
-Another shard?
-Koga?
KAGOME: No.
This one feels different.
-Is it Kohaku?
-I committed many evil acts
under Naraku's control.
I killed my family and caused
my only sister great injury
and overwhelming grief.
However, I kept myself
alive the entire time.
-All for the sake
of revenge, huh?
-Yes.
It's my duty.
And I must fulfill
it before I die.
It's the only way I
can make up for what
I did to my father and comrades.
-It's useless, Kohaku.
Can't you see it doesn't
matter how determined you are?
Your blade will never
be enough to overcome
Naraku, the infant,
or Hakudoshi.
In the end, you're doomed to
lose your shard and your life.
-Exactly right.
-Kagura.
-(VOICEOVER) As for me,
my loyalty now lies with
the infant, rather than Naraku.
There's no such thing
as true freedom.
-Please, Kagura.
You must take me to his heart.
If you don't, I'll go alone.
No!
What are you doing?
-There.
Now you've lost the means
to find Naraku's heart.
-Kagura-- why?
-Shut up and go!
Run away before you lose your
shard and your life, you fool.
-Such an untrustworthy woman.
You intend to betray Naraku,
and then betray us, too?
-Run, Kohaku!
-But--
-I said run!
Kohaku, try not to hurt
yourself on the way down.
-Kagura!
-He won't get away.
-Dance of the Dragon!
-Kagura, how'd you like
to taste your own blades?
See how you like them?
[gasp]
INUYASHA: Wind Scar!
-Inuyasha!
-What the hell's going on?
I thought you and Hakudoshi
were on the same side.
-What makes you think
it's any of your business?
-Sango, you'd better
go after Kohaku.
-Got it.
Let's go, Kirara.
-Adamant Barrage!
-I can still sense
the shard, you guys.
He must still be
in the vicinity.
-Shouldn't you be a bit
more careful, Inuyasha?
-I will split you in half
if you try anything funny.
-Listen up, I want you tell
us everything you know.
You might as well do it
while you have the chance.
Hakdoshi's not going anywhere
until he's finished you off.
-True.
He doesn't want me to reveal
the location of Naraku's heart.
Here he comes.
-It's Goryomaru.
He's still alive?
-Who's responsible for
those who injuries?
-None of that matters right now.
-Huh?
-I have come to get
the Shikon jewel shard.
-Goryomaru is Moryomaru?
-Use this
KAGOME: A Shikon jewel shard!
HAKUDOSHI: I'll take
care of these ones.
You need to go and
find that other shard.
-Your'e not going anywhere!
Hakudoshi!
An illusion?
-Traitor.
-Huh?
-Did you really believe
I would let you escape?
-Get back here!
Bastard!
-Go on.
What are you waiting for?
Is it Kagura?
-(VOICEOVER) he won't do it?
What a pathetic fool.
-I'm surprised.
I didn't think I could
use you as a shield.
-Fool!
We don't have much
time, so listen up.
Naraku's heart, the infant,
is inside Moryomaru.
-What?
-Hakudoshi and the infant intend
to empower Moryomaru and have
him overthrow Naraku.
-An impressive
deduction, Kagura.
It was a grave
mistake for Naraku
to release his heart that day.
He entrusted the Fuyoheki to the
infant to keep his heart safe,
knowing it would conceal
its demonic aura.
That gave the infant an idea.
To create a durable
armor to protect himself.
And that armor is Moryomaru, who
swallowed the dead Goryomaru.
It was at that point
that we realized,
Naraku without his heart
is but an empty shell.
The infant and I
are the real thing.
And one day soon,
we'll overthrow him.
-Naraku has been
aware of your plot
from the very beginning, fool.
-No doubt.
But if I were you, I'd be more
concerned about my own fate
right now.
After all, we may
both be traitors,
but it is your
heart Naraku holds.
It's hopeless for you.
No matter what,
you'll never be free.
-Shut up!
-You can rip my body to pieces.
I still won't die.
Nobody can kill me.
Not even Naraku himself.
[laughter]
-What?
-Take this!
Wind Scar!
-Right.
-You're using your Wind Tunnel?
-Too late.
Hold on.
Why aren't they protecting me?
KAGURA: Well, well.
Isn't this interesting?
It looks like Naraku's
given up on you.
-Silence.
I cannot be killed.
-Look out!
-I'll purify it.
-I'm not like you, Kagura!
I cannot be used up and
thrown away like that!
-Run, Kagura!
-I am--
-Wind Tunnel!
-I am his essence!
-I have a very bad feeling.
-Huh?
-It's as if Naraku planned
for this to happen.
-He probably did.
It makes sense.
Naraku decided to let us take
care of Hakudoshi for him.
-So, now what will you do?
You could come with
us if you wanted.
-No thanks.
I can't go with
you, or with anyone.
Anyway, you don't
have time to waste.
It won't be long before
Moryomaru finds Kohaku.
-She's got a point there.
-Come on, Kagome.
We have to go.
-Y-- yeah.
-Listen, Kagura.
I'm going to make sure
that we get your heart back
from Naraku, so
just hang in there.
All right?
-Who do you think
you're kidding?
-Just promise me you won't
die before it happens!
You got that?
-I don't need you to tell
me to run for my life.
I'll go as far as I have to.
-(ECHOING) Kohaku!
-Sister, please just keep going.
Huh?
Whoa!
[laughter]
-I can see what's in your heart.
Haunted by the memories of
killing your own family.
You seek atonement by
giving your own life.
How very noble.
Then you shall die for
the sake of your sister.
For that woman will forget how
her brother killed her father
in cold blood.
SANGO: Kohaku!
-As long as you
live, both of you
will continue to
suffer this torment.
-Sister--
SANGO: Hiraikotsu!
-Huh?
-Stay away, sister!
-Kohaku!
So you do remember.
-Your resistance is pointless.
-You're the one who's fighting
a losing battle, Moryomaru.
Or should I say, Naraku's heart?
-Huh?
-Now that we know
your identity, we'll
never allow you to escape.
Prepare yourself!
Adamant Barrage!
You're gonna run away?
-Inuyasha, it's only
a matter of time
before I absorb the demonic
power that's in your blade.
-Huh?
-Coward.
-I can't sense the shard now.
He got away.
-That was close.
SANGO: Kohaku?
You recognize me, don't you?
-Huh?
-Tell me that you do.
Tell me.
-I remember.
Everything.
From that day.
And for that reason, I
can't stay with you, sister.
-Kohaku--
-Why not?
I mean, you just got here.
-Kohaku!
What will that accomplish, huh?
You're just going
to go off and die?
-Maybe.
KAGOME: But it hurts
too much to be together.
-Kagome.
-Being with Sango reminds
you of what you did, huh?
She still loves you.
For her, no one else in the
world could take your place.
-I'm so sorry.
-Kohaku--
-I guess even you
wouldn't be able to fill
the void in Sango's
heart, Miroku.
-I will have you know
that nobody could ever
take my place, either.
-Huh?
-Lady Kikyo.
-Are you in much pain?
-Don't worry.
It's just a scratch.
-M--m-- master, look!
-Spirits?
-She's looking straight at us!
-So you can see me.
How interesting.
-Stay back!
Begone, demon!
-I'm afraid your demon repelling
charms have no effect on me.
-So sorry!
Please don't kill me!
-Spirits!
-Somehow those two breached
Lady Kikyo's barrier.
-I don't understand how
they got through it.
Lady Kiyko?
-(VOICEOVER) At this rate, I
won't be able to defeat Naraku
before I--
KANNA: As I pass though the
lengthy struggle of life
in this fleeting world, I cannot
help but long for the midnight
moon I once saw.
[theme music]
KAGOME: Kikyo attempts
to use Midoriko's soul
to stay alive long
enough to destroy Naraku.
Meanwhile, Koga tries
to obtain the Goraishi
from the grave of his ancestors.
With Hakudoshi now eliminated,
will Narkau's next target
be Kagura?
INUYASHA: I can
smell Kagura's blood.
Naraku holds her heart!
Next time on Inuyasha, The
Final Act, Kagura's Wind.
KAGURA: I am the
wind, the free wind.