[theme music]
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER)
I'm going to make sure
that we get your heart
back from Naraku.
Just promise me you won't
die before it happens!
-(VOICEOVER) I'll
run for my life.
I'll go as far as I have to.
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER)
Kagura's Wind.
SANGO: This one here
is father's grave.
The others are
buried beside him.
So you see, they're
resting in peace, Kohaku.
-But I can't forgive myself.
-(VOICEOVER) I guess he
wasn't ready to see this yet.
MIROKU: Myoga, is
this the location
of the anomaly you spoke of?
MYOGA: Mm-hm.
-This is Midoriko's cave.
Midoriko was a priestess who
lived hundreds of years ago.
She was a demon slayer.
Eventually, she found a
way to destroy the demons,
but it cost her her life.
She absorbed the demons'
souls into herself,
forcing out her own.
The crystallization of her soul
is known as the Shikon jewel.
-That hole in her chest-- is
it supposed to be doing that?
-You're right.
It's shining.
-There's something inside it.
It looks like a chrysalis.
-I'll take a closer look.
-Huh?
-There's some kind
of barrier around it.
-Oh, dear!
This must be an ill omen.
There can be no
other explanation.
-Yeah.
We should probably keep an
eye on this place for a while.
(VOICEOVER) That scent.
Could it be?
BOY: Are you serious
about this, Koga?
BOY: The most powerful weapon
known to the wolf demon
tribe, the Goraishi,
is enshrined
in the deepest part
of this burial ground.
-That's perfect.
Once I can get my
hands on Gorai-thing,
I should have no problem
beating the life out
of Naraku and Moryomaru.
-It's as if he's not
listening to a word we say.
-Careful not to incite
the wrath of the gods.
-Great.
Let's get going.
-Aw.
-I'd never leave you behind.
-So, Inuyasha stayed behind?
-Yeah.
-It could just be me, but
it seemed like he really
didn't want anyone else around.
-What?
-It's not just you.
I valiantly offered
my unwavering support
to stay with Inuyasha, and he
all but chased me away, too.
-You know, come to think
of it, that barrier
didn't strike me as evil.
In truth, it felt pure to me.
-Huh?
(VOICEOVER) Does that mean--
Huh?
A soul collector!
So it was Kikyo, after all.
-(VOICEOVER) Naraku's
miasma is persistent.
Even Kagome's purification
was not enough.
-Kikyo!
Inuyasha.
I take it you followed
the soul collector?
-Kikyo, what do you intend
to do with Midoriko's soul?
-This is what Naraku inflicted
upon me at Mount Hakurei.
-But weren't you healed?
-For a short time, yes.
But as you can see, the
wound has now reopened.
This is the reason why I
have taken Midoriko's soul.
Using it is the
only option I have.
Otherwise, I'll be
consumed by the miasma.
This body will return to the
earth before I defeat Naraku.
Even though Midoriko's
soul is dead,
I know that it will
help me stay alive long
enough to complete my task.
Midoriko was a priestess
who died slaying demons.
In many ways, you could say
that we share the same soul.
I am sure she'd understand
my reasons for doing this.
-Kikyo.
Kikyo!
(VOICEOVER) Her
wound is healing.
-What?
Huh?
(VOICEOVER) Kohaku's Shikon
jewel shard is-- Kohaku!
-This is going to
hurt for a while.
-Kohaku!
Wait!
-Those are Kikyo's
soul collectors!
-That's right.
And thy appear to
be guiding Kohaku.
A barrier?
Do you think this
is Kikyo's to doing?
-No.
It's not. (VOICEOVER) I think
I know who put this barrier up.
-Kohaku, come back!
-Don't worry, sister!
(VOICEOVER) The shard
is telling me to go.
It's telling me defeat Naraku.
I don't care what it takes.
I'll do anything
to accomplish that!
-What is it, Koga?
-It's nothing.
-(VOICEOVER) What is this?
My legs-- the
Shikon jewel shards
feel so heavy all of a sudden.
-Are you gonna be OK?
That wound isn't gonna
reopen again, is it?
-I cannot be sure.
That is why I must make haste.
-Can't you just wait
until I defeat Naraku?
-You cannot defeat
Naraku with a sword.
-Huh?
-Please, listen to me.
Defeating Naraku
requires the obliteration
of his entire being,
including his soul.
It doesn't make a
difference how many times
you destroy his body.
Naraku was created
when demons were
merged into the vile soul
of the thief Onigumo.
From the beginning,
he's had no true body,
so the Shikon jewel is
perhaps one and only power
great enough to
eradicate Naraku's soul.
The Shikon jewel must
be restored at once.
There is no other way.
There will only be one chance.
When Naraku obtains the
restored Shikon jewel,
the jewel will be defiled
within Naraku's hands
as it fuses with him.
In that instant, we must purify
Naraku, along with the jewel.
And only I am capable of this.
-Wait!
Kikyo!
-Inuyasha, now is not
the time for hesitation.
And it is too late
now to turn back.
(VOICEOVER) Restoring
the Shikon jewel
would mean taking
Kohaku's shard.
And to do that, you'd
have to take his life.
Kikyo, you're not
the kind of person
who's capable of that-- are you?
Huh?
-I understand now.
I know what I have to do.
So I'm going.
-(VOICEOVER) I don't get it.
Why didn't I notice Kohaku's
scent when he was so close?
-Please explain to the others.
-Huh?
Kohaku!
-I'm not going there to die.
I'm going there
to defeat Naraku.
Please, take care of my sister.
-Kohaku.
-Who dares wake me
from my slumber?
-Meioju, I am here
because your shell
is said to be the
ultimate armor.
You will give it to me.
-Devour him, Moryomaru.
Very good, Meioju.
Now you've become
my ultimate armor.
-It feels like we're grave
robbers, or something.
-Koga!
Over there!
-That's it!
KOGA: The Goraishi of
the wolf demon tribe.
-Whoa!
-None shall pass
beyond this point.
-It talked!
-Let's get this over with. 'Kay?
-Look, we aren't
thieves, or anything.
-We've just come to
borrow the Goraishi.
-Never!
It belongs to the
wolf demon tribe,
and contains centuries
of our brethrens' souls.
If you desire it--
-I have to defeat you.
Right?
-Prepare to be incinerated!
-Not again!
[shouting]
-He got him!
-That's Koga for you.
-Cursed rat!
You're using Shikon
jewel shards?
-So what if I am?
What did you think, I
was gonna take 'em out?
They're part of me.
-Part of your body?
Those shards you
possess are controlled
by the will of that which is
no longer part of this world.
And the Goraishi you
desire is controlled
by souls which have rested
here since ancient times.
Souls that are also no
longer part of this world.
Like those jewel
shards, the Goraishi
is not for you to weild.
-Enough of this nonsense!
-Now burn!
-Too slow!
-You cannot win.
-We'll see about that!
-Whoa!
-All right.
I've almost got him.
-You shall not pass!
-Ah!
Get back!
[nervous shouts]
-Whoa!
-Gotcha.
[screaming]
-Huh?
-I'm comin'!
I almost lost you two.
-Sorry about that.
-Pathetic fools.
Behold!
-Koga, the Goraishi!
It's gone!
-You should have
abandoned your friends
and obtained the Goraishi
when you had the chance.
-If you think I
regret my choice,
then you don't know me at all.
-What?
-Listen up!
The only reason I came
for your precious Goraishi
is because I plan to use
it to avenge my tribe.
But if it means
sacrificing my comrades,
then I don't need the Goraishi.
Got it, moron?
-Koga.
I'd follow you anywhere.
-Enough of your preaching!
You shall pay for desecrating
this burial ground
and disturbing the ancient ones!
-I'll show you disturbing!
-Whoa!
-The Goraishi!
-When did that happen?
-Take this!
[scream]
-(VOICEOVER) How did I--
-The Goraishi will
be your claws.
From this day forth,
you shall have
the protection of our souls.
-(VOICEOVER) It disappeared?
But no-- it merged with my body.
It's part of me now.
-What was all that about?
-Does this mean our ancestors
will watch over him?
GORAISHI SPIRIT: However, know
that we can only protect you
once from the power which
controls the Shikon jewel
shards in your legs.
The power which is not
a part of this world.
-(VOICEOVER) I'll be
sure to remember that.
[gasp]
-Naraku.
-Kagua, apparently
Hakudoshi has died.
-(VOICEOVER) You know it
couldn't have happened if you
didn't want it to.
-He was nothing but a
fool, that Hakudoshi.
It seems that he thought
he could destroy me.
Kagura, I shall grant
you your freedom.
-Huh?
So, you'll grant me my freedom?
-You wish to be
liberated from me.
Do you not?
Isn't that why you
disobeyed my orders,
allowed Goryomaru to escape, and
allied yourself with Hakudoshi?
-If you were aware of it,
then why-- m-- my heart!
-That's right.
If I were to return
this to your body,
you would no longer be
under anyone's control.
Not even mine.
You'd be free at last.
-(VOICEOVER) It's back.
[gasp]
-Not to worry.
I was careful to avoid
hitting your precious heart.
-Naraku-- you bastard!
[laughter]
-Now you may go.
Wherever you wish.
-Damn.
That-- that bastard.
He's cursed my body with miasma.
NARAKU: Enjoy what little
time you have left to live.
Of course, it will be filled
with only pain and despair.
You didn't honestly believe
you deserved a better
fate than this, did you, Kagura?
You longed for freedom.
Well, now you have it.
-Lord Sesshomaru, the
demonic aura from the crystal
is weakening.
That can only mean that
Naraku's heart is nearby.
-Oh. look.
There's a cave up ahead.
-Stay back.
-Hm.
You're Inuyasha's
brother, aren't you?
-I have never considered
that lowly half demon
to be my brother.
But the fact that you know
even that much tells me
that you are Naraku's heart.
Are you not?
-Hmph.
Sesshomaru, you'll regret that.
Wielding your sword
before greeting me?
-That I doubt.
But you will regret uttering
Inuyasha's name in my presence.
That much I promise you.
-Ah-- only need a day to
recover from these wounds.
[heartbeat]
(VOICEOVER) My heart.
I can feel it beating.
I can go wherever I want.
I'm-- free.
-That armor!
The Tokijin didn't
even scratch it.
-Keep swinging that
sword of yours.
In time, I will absorb all
of your demonic energy.
I suppose I can't let
you have all the fun.
-This is terrible.
He's getting stronger
with every one
of Lord Sesshomaru's attacks.
Aren't we supposed
to be helping him?
-You fool!
Can't you see this is all part
of Lord Sesshomaru's master
plan?
-So what's his plan?
-Idiot!
If I knew that, you think my
life would be this difficult?
-It won't work, Sesshomaru.
-Hm?
-I shall absorb
your demonic energy.
No sense prolonging
this any further.
-No-- why is my body failing me?
The wound has reopened.
And I don't have enough
energy left in me to heal it.
[shivering]
-This scent.
-Hm?
So that useless
woman died, did she?
First she betrayed
Naraku, and then me.
All because she
wanted her freedom.
And then when she finally
gets it, what does she do?
She dies.
And dies in vain, at that.
-Silence.
-But-- that's impossible.
My shell is impenetrable.
-See?
Just as I expected.
-Way to go!
You've almost got him!
-The demonic energy
that I absorbed!
-The demonic energy you
absorbed could never
be contained in that pitiful
vessel you call a body.
Take this.
Azure Dragonwave!
-Argh!
This isn't good.
The Shikon jewel shard--
-The Tokijin!
-It snapped?
-This isn't over.
I will be back for you.
-Hmph.
-Lord Sesshomaru!
-I'm so glad you're safe!
Hello?
Lord Sesshomaru?
-You're not going to
leave your sword, are you?
-I have no attachment
to a broken sword.
I will find a replacement.
-I don't understand.
Where is Lord Sesshomaru going?
-A flower?
INUYASHA: I'm sure of it.
That's the scent
of Kagura's blood.
-Perhaps Naraku found out
that she betrayed him.
-Let us hurry.
-(VOICEOVER) Why did't we
force her to stay with us?
We should've known better than
to let Kagura go off alone.
KAGURA: It's so quiet.
No one is in sight.
Is this how it ends?
All by myself?
Is this the freedom
that I longed for?
You-- you came.
-I followed this scent
of blood and miasma.
-Oh.
I see.
You thought I was Naraku.
Disappointed that it's not him?
-No.
I knew it was you.
-I see.
(VOICEOVER) So you came.
You came here to see me.
-(VOICEOVER) Even
Tenseiga cannot save her.
Are you leaving?
-Yes.
I've had enough.
(VOICEOVER) Now that I've
seen you one last time.
INUYASHA: Wait!
Sesshomaru.
-Inuyasha?
-Kagura.
Did she suffer?
-She was smiling.
KAGURA: I am the wind.
The free wind.
[theme music]
KAGOME: Shippo attempts the
Fox Demon Promotion Exam
at the demon mansion
known as the Fox Inn.
-That must be it.
Does that mean I'll
advance in rank
every time I beat up Inuyasha?
KAGOME: Meanwhile,
Tenseiga is making
life difficult for Sesshomaru.
What's gonna happen
now, Totosai?
INUYASHA: Next time on
Inuyasha, The Final Act,
Meido Zangetsuha.
SESSHOMARU: I now
wield the Tenseiga.
Ready for battle.