Sinon: SO DEATH GUN
WAS IN LAUGHING COFFIN,
AND YOU GUYS FOUGHT BEFORE.
KIRITO,
I NEED TO KNOW SOMETHING.
IT'S ABOUT
THE PEOPLE YOU KILLED.
HOW DID YOU GET OVER
WHAT YOU DID?
HOW ARE YOU
NOT AFFECTED BY IT?
HOW ARE YOU SO STRONG,
YOU'RE NOT CONTROLLED BY IT?
Kirito: I HAVEN'T
GOTTEN OVER IT.
Sinon: WHAT?
Kirito: LAST NIGHT,
I KEPT HAVING NIGHTMARES
ABOUT THE THREE GUYS I KILLED.
I HARDLY SLEPT AT ALL.
I SAW THEIR FACES
RIGHT BEFORE THEY VANISHED.
I HEARD THEIR VOICES,
THEIR WORDS.
I DON'T THINK
I'M EVER GONNA FORGET 'EM.
Sinon: (GASPS)
BUT THEN...
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
I‐‐I CAN'T...
Kirito: IT'S OKAY.
I THINK THAT'S PROBABLY
HOW IT SHOULD BE.
I GET IT NOW.
THERE ARE THINGS
I SHOULDN'T FORGET,
WHAT IT MEANS TO KILL,
THE SIGNIFICANCE
OF TAKING A LIFE.
AND ONCE I ACCEPT IT,
MAYBE THEN I'LL BE ABLE
TO FIND SOME CLOSURE.
THAT'S HOW I SEE IT.
Sinon: CLOSURE...
BY ACCEPTING IT?
(SIGHS)
(WIND BLOWING)
Sinon: DEATH GUN.
Kirito: HMM?
Sinon: IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT UNDER THAT CLOAK,
THERE'S A REAL‐LIVE PERSON
WHO JUST WANTS TO KILL.
Kirito: YEAH.
AND IF I KNEW
HIS HANDLE IN "S. A. O.,"
I'D BE ABLE TO FIGURE OUT
HIS NAME AND ADDRESS
IN THE REAL WORLD.
THAT'S THE REASON
WHY I LOGGED INTO "G. G. O."
Sinon: OH.
THEN MAYBE
HIS REASON FOR BEING HERE
IS 'CAUSE HE LIKES TO P.K.
MAYBE HE MISSES THE RUSH
OF DOING IT FROM "S. A. O."
YOU THINK?
Kirito: NAH,
THERE'S MORE TO IT THAN THAT.
HE KILLED ZXE‐D AND TARAKO
IN FRONT
OF A BUNCH OF WITNESSES.
IT WAS THE SAME WITH PALE RIDER.
HE ALWAYS PICKS TIMES WHEN HE'S
GOT THE BIGGEST AUDIENCE.
AND THAT SIGN OF THE CROSS
HE MAKES,
I BET HE DOES IT TO FREAK OUT
AS MANY PEOPLE AS POSSIBLE.
HE WANTS YOU TO BELIEVE
HE'S GOT THE POWER TO KILL YOU
FROM IN THE GAME,
BUT IT'S ALL A SHOW.
Sinon: IF THAT'S TRUE,
THEN HOW'S HE KILLING PEOPLE?
Kirito: IT'S NOT
'CAUSE OF BRAIN DAMAGE
FROM THEIR HEADGEAR.
THE AUTHORITIES SAID
THAT ZXE‐D AND TARAKO
DIED OF HEART FAILURE.
Sinon: HEART FAILURE?
MY GOD.
Kirito: TO BE HONEST,
I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW HE KILLED 'EM EITHER.
BUT THE THOUGHT OF FIRING
A GUN IN THE VIRTUAL WORLD
AND STOPPING A PLAYER'S HEART,
THERE'S NO WAY THAT'S POSSIBLE.
HANG ON A SECOND.
COME TO THINK OF IT...
Sinon: WHAT?
Kirito: THAT WAS WEIRD.
Sinon: WHAT WAS?
Kirito: BACK THERE IN THE RUINS,
HE HAD HIS HANDGUN OUT FOR YOU,
BUT HE SWITCHED
TO THE RIFLE FOR ME,
BUT HE KILLS WITH THE HANDGUN.
HE COULD HAVE KILLED ME WITH IT,
SO WHY'D HE SWITCH?
Sinon: YEAH. GOOD QUESTION.
Kirito: COULD IT BE
THAT HE DIDN'T SHOOT ME WITH IT
'CAUSE HE COULDN'T
SHOOT ME WITH IT?
THE HANDGUN,
CAN'T USE IT, THOUGH.
THE SWITCH.
THE CROSSING HIMSELF THING.
INVISIBILITY CLOAK.
CONDITIONS, RULES.
Kikuoka: HERE.
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW RELIEVED I AM
TO HEAR YOU PUT IT INTO WORDS.
Kirito: KNEW IT.
IN‐GAME GUNS CAN'T KILL I. R. L.
SHOOTING SOMEONE
FROM IN HERE'S NOT WHAT DOES IT.
IT TAKES PREPARATION.
Sinon: NOW YOU LOST ME.
Kirito: THE ONLY WAY
TO MAKE IT LOOK
LIKE HE'S KILLING PEOPLE IN‐GAME
IS BY SETTING UP FOR THE MURDER
IN THE REAL WORLD FIRST.
Sinon: HOW WOULD HE
SET SOMETHING LIKE THAT UP?
I MEAN, IF YOU'RE RIGHT,
HE'D HAVE TO GET A PLAYER'S
REAL‐LIFE INFORMATION TO DO IT.
ALL THAT STUFF'S SECURE, THOUGH.
Kirito: NO.
IF SOMEONE'S CLEVER ENOUGH,
THEY CAN FIND OUT
A PLAYER'S ADDRESS EASY.
Sinon: HOW?
Kirito: THE TERMINALS
AT THE GOVERNOR'S OFFICE.
YOU HAVE TO PLUG YOUR REAL NAME
AND ADDRESS INTO 'EM TO COMPETE.
IT'S AN OPEN SPACE.
YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY PRIVACY THERE.
Sinon: NO WAY. YOU SAYING
HE PEEKED OVER THEIR SHOULDERS
WHILE THEY ENTERED THEIR INFO?
THAT CAN'T BE IT,
'CAUSE YOU'D NOTICE
SOMEONE LURKING NEXT TO YOU.
Kirito: HE COULD HAVE
USED A SCOPE
OR SOME BINOCULARS
FROM ACROSS THE ROOM.
Sinon: THAT'S
BREAKING ETIQUETTE.
HE'D GET HIS ASS
KICKED OUT OF THE GAME FOR THAT.
Kirito: THEN HOW 'BOUT THIS?
MAYBE DEATH GUN CAN,
LIKE, USE HIS CLOAK
TO TURN INVISIBLE IN TOWN, TOO.
Sinon: HE'D BE RIGHT THERE,
AND YOU WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW IT.
BUT STILL, HE CAN'T
DO ANYTHING IN THE REAL WORLD.
WHEN HE'S LOGGED IN HERE,
HE'S UNCONSCIOUS THERE.
Kirito: RIGHT.
(GASPS)
WAIT.
THAT'S IT. YEAH.
IT'S NOT JUST HIM.
DEATH GUN...
HAS A PARTNER!
CHECK IT OUT.
ONE OF THEM PLAYS
AS THE DEATH GUN AVATAR.
HIS JOB IS TO SHOOT THE TARGET.
AT THE SAME TIME,
IN THE REAL WORLD,
THE SECOND PERSON
IN THE TARGET'S APARTMENT.
HIS JOB IS TAKE THE PLAYER OUT.
Sinon: (GASPS)
OKAY, BUT LET'S SAY
THEY FOUND OUT YOUR ADDRESS.
WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER PEOPLE
LIVING THERE?
AND THEY'D NEED A KEY.
Kirito: AS FAR
AS ZXE‐D AND TARAKO GO,
THEY LIVED ALONE,
AND THEIR APARTMENTS
WERE IN OLDER BUILDINGS.
THE E‐LOCKS ON THEIR DOORS
WERE PROBABLY FIRST‐GEN,
NOT VERY SECURE.
BESIDES, THEY WERE BOTH DIVING
IN "G. G. O." DURING THE BREAK‐IN,
SO THEY WERE BOTH UNCONSCIOUS
AND COMPLETELY HELPLESS.
THEY COULDN'T HEAR,
SO THE KILLER COULD
TAKE HIS TIME GETTING IN.
Sinon: BUT THEN YOU SAID
THE CAUSE OF DEATH FOR BOTH
WAS HEART FAILURE, RIGHT?
SO HOW'D THEY
STOP SOMEONE'S HEART
IN A WAY BOTH THE COPS AND
THE CORONER COULDN'T FIGURE OUT?
Kirito: MAYBE BY INJECTING
SOME KIND OF DRUG OR SOMETHING.
THAT'S ONE WAY.
Sinon: OKAY, BUT SOMEONE
SHOULD HAVE FOUND
EVIDENCE OF IT,
A MARK OR SOMETHING.
Kirito: THEY DIDN'T
FIND THE BODIES FOR A WHILE,
SO THEY WERE PRETTY DECOMPOSED.
BESIDES, A HARD‐CORE GAMER
CAN GO FOR DAYS
WITHOUT EATING OR SLEEPING.
I DOUBT ANYONE
WOULD THINK IT'S WEIRD
IF SOMEONE DIED
OF A HEART ATTACK AFTER THAT.
Sinon: THEY'RE CRAZY.
RIGHT?
I MEAN, WHY ELSE
WOULD ANYONE DO THIS?
Kirito: MAYBE,
OR MAYBE THEY DO IT
'CAUSE RED PLAYERS
ARE WHO THEY REALLY ARE.
I MEAN, DEEP DOWN,
I THINK I'M REALLY A SWORDSMAN.
Sinon: WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT WAY,
I CAN SORT OF UNDERSTAND.
THERE'S TIMES WHEN I THINK
I'M A REAL SNIPER, NOT A GAMER.
WAIT. DO YOU THINK
THE GUY DOING THE KILLING'S
A RED PLAYER, TOO,
YOU KNOW, LIKE DEATH GUN?
Kirito: YEAH. THEY WERE PROBABLY
IN LAUGHING COFFIN TOGETHER.
I'M STILL WONDERING HOW THEY
COORDINATED THE KILLINGS
BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE REAL ONE.
HOW ARE THEY
SO PRECISE ABOUT IT?
‐ YEAH.
‐ Sinon: (GASPS)
Kirito: THAT'S IT.
THAT'S WHAT DOING
THE SIGN OF THE CROSS IS ABOUT.
IT'S NOT JUST FOR SHOW.
IT'S ALSO A GREAT OPPORTUNITY
TO SNEAK A PEEK AT HIS WATCH.
Sinon: YOU'RE RIGHT.
(GASPS)
Kirito: SINON...
DO YOU LIVE ALONE?
Sinon: UM, YEAH.
BUT I'M SURE I LOCKED MY DOOR.
MY BUILDING'S
GOT FIRST‐GEN LOCKS,
BUT I'VE ALSO GOT A CHAIN.
(GASPS)
I THINK I LEFT
THE CHAIN OFF TONIGHT.
Kirito: OH, MAN.
LISTEN,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LIKE THIS.
WHEN DEATH GUN
WAS CHASING US ON THAT HORSE,
I WASN'T THE ONE
HE WAS SHOOTING AT.
AND THAT COULD ONLY MEAN
THEY GOT THEIR NEXT VICTIM
ALL SET UP AND READY TO GO.
Sinon: OKAY.
THEN WHO'S NEXT?
Kirito: I GOT A FEELING THAT
RIGHT NOW IN THE REAL WORLD,
DEATH GUN'S PARTNER'S
IN YOUR PLACE.
HE'S WATCHING THE LIVE STREAM,
WAITING FOR WHEN YOU
GET SHOT BY THAT GUN.
IT'S JUST A HUNCH.
(LIZARD SQUEALS)
Sinon: NO.
NO. NO, NOT THAT.
OH, GOD. (GASPING)
(HEART BEATING)
Kirito: CALM DOWN.
IF YOU LOG OUT NOW,
YOU'LL BE IN DANGER.
JUST CALM DOWN.
GO EASY.
(HEARTBEAT SLOWING)
UNTIL DEATH GUN SHOOTS YOU,
THE GUY IN YOUR PLACE
ISN'T GONNA DO ANYTHING, OKAY?
THAT'S THE RULE
THEY SET UP FOR THEMSELVES.
BUT IF YOU LOG OUT NOW AND
WAKE UP WITH HIS PARTNER THERE,
HE'LL KILL YOU,
SO YOU HAVE TO CALM DOWN.
Sinon: BUT‐‐BUT...
I'M SCARED. I'M SO SCARED.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
All: HMM?
Lisbeth: JEEZ, CHRYSHEIGHT,
TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
Kikuoka: SORRY, GUYS.
I BOOKED IT OVER HERE
AS FAST AS I COULD
FROM MY SAVE POINT.
IF THERE WERE
A SPEED LIMIT IN "A. L. O.,"
MY LICENSE WOULD HAVE
GOTTEN SUSPENDED.
HUH?
Asuna: WHAT IS GOING ON?
Kikuoka: (CLEARS THROAT)
I'D BE HAPPY
TO EXPLAIN IN DETAIL,
BUT I SHOULD WARN YOU
IT MIGHT TAKE A WHILE.
TO TELL THE TRUTH, I'M NOT
100% SURE WHERE TO BEGIN.
Asuna: OH, DON'T EVEN.
Yui: NOT TO WORRY.
I KNOW JUST WHERE TO START.
ON NOVEMBER 9,
IN "GUN GALE ONLINE,"
A PLAYER CALLED DEATH GUN
FIRED HIS WEAPON
AT AN AVATAR
APPEARING ON A MONITOR.
THAT SAME DAY IN NAKANO WARD,
THE PLAYER OF THAT AVATAR
MYSTERIOUSLY DIED.
Kikuoka: YOUNG LADY,
THAT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
GATHERING ALL THAT INFORMATION
AND CONNECTING IT SO QUICKLY,
YOU MUST BE
QUITE THE RESEARCHER.
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
A CAREER IN THE V. R. SECTION?
‐ Asuna: (GROANS)
‐ Kikuoka: WHOA. YOU WIN.
I'M SORRY. I'M NOT GOING
TO STONEWALL YOU, PROMISE.
JUST COMPLIMENTING HER, IS ALL.
SHE'S RIGHT, THOUGH. IT'S TRUE.
Klein: YO,
CHRYSHEIGHT OR WHATEVER,
I HEAR YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT HIRED KIRITO
TO DIVE INTO THAT GAME.
SO LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU GOT HIM TO CONVERT OVER
KNOWING A PLAYER
GOT SHOT IN‐GAME
AND DIED I. R. L. BECAUSE OF IT?
Kikuoka: EASY, KLEIN.
I CAN EXPLAIN.
THAT'S NOT HOW THE PLAYER DIED.
Klein: THEN HOW?
Kikuoka: IT'S NOT
THE AMUSPHERE RIG.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS TO YOU
IN‐GAME, IT CAN'T HURT YOU,
AND IT CERTAINLY
CAN'T STOP A PLAYER'S HEART
WHEN IT'S NOT EVEN
DIRECTLY CONNECTED TO IT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
KIRITO AND I MET LAST WEEK
TO TALK ABOUT IT AND PRETTY MUCH
AGREED IT WAS IMPOSSIBLE.
THERE'S NO WAY ANYONE
CAN KILL A PERSON IN REAL LIFE
BY SHOOTING THEM IN THE GAME.
Leafa: OKAY, THEN,
IF WHAT YOU SAY IS TRUE,
HOW COME YOU HAD MY BROTHER
DIVE INTO "G. G. O." FOR YOU, HUH?
YOU HAD A HUNCH
SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
SCRATCH THAT.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING'S WRONG.
THAT DEATH GUN GUY'S
A PART OF IT,
AND I BET YOU SENT MY BROTHER IN
TO TRY TO FIND HIM.
Asuna: CHRYSHEIGHT,
WE FIGURED IT OUT.
DEATH GUN IS AN "S. A. O."
SURVIVOR JUST LIKE US,
BUT UNLIKE US,
HE WAS A RED PLAYER
WHO WAS IN A GUILD OF KILLERS
CALLED LAUGHING COFFIN.
Kikuoka: YOU SURE
HE WAS WITH THEM?
Asuna: YES. NONE OF US
CAN REMEMBER HIS NAME, THOUGH.
KLEIN AND I MET HIM ONCE
WHEN OUR GROUP
WENT TO CAPTURE HIS.
Lisbeth: UM, HEY, ASUNA,
I GET THE FEELING
CHRYSHEIGHT KNOWS MORE
THAN HE'S LETTING ON.
NO OFFENSE, CHRYSHEIGHT,
BUT ALL WE KNOW
IS YOU WORK FOR THE GOVERNMENT
DOING SOMETHING WITH NETWORKS
AND THAT YOU PLAY "A. L. O."
AS PART OF SOME KIND OF RESEARCH
YOU'RE DOING ON V. R. M. M. O. s.
Kikuoka: ONLY FOR THE PAST YEAR.
THE JOB I HAD BEFORE
WAS A LITTLE...
DIFFERENT.
I USED TO BE PART
OF THE TASK FORCE
FOR THE "S. A. O." INCIDENT.
BUT EVEN THOUGH
WE WERE CALLED A TASK FORCE,
IN THE END,
WE WERE PRETTY INEFFECTIVE.
Asuna: CHRYSHEIGHT,
YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY WELL CONNECTED,
AND WITH A LITTLE DIGGING,
YOU COULD FIND OUT
WHAT THE REAL‐LIFE NAME AND
ADDRESS OF THIS DEATH GUN IS.
JUST MAKE A LIST OF THE HANDLES
OF ALL THE SURVIVING
LAUGHING COFFIN MEMBERS.
THEN CONTACT THEIR I. S. P. s,
ASK WHICH ONE'S
PLAYING "G. G. O." NOW,
AND TRACE THEIR LOCATION.
Kikuoka: NO. SORRY,
THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
THE I. S. P. s
AREN'T GOING TO GIVE OUT
A PLAYER'S REAL‐LIFE INFO
IF ALL WE HAVE TO GO ON
ARE THEIR HANDLES.
Silica: MAYBE IF WE ASK
THE GAME'S ADMINS,
THEY COULD HELP.
Kikuoka: THEY MIGHT,
BUT "G. G. O.'s" ADMINS
ARE IN THE U. S.,
SO IT'LL BE A WHILE
BEFORE WE GOT AN ANSWER.
Leafa: I KNOW MY BROTHER,
AND RIGHT NOW, HE'S RISKING
HIS LIFE IN THAT GAME,
TRYING TO FIND OUT
WHO THIS PERSON IS.
WHEN HE CAME HOME LAST NIGHT,
HE HAD THIS LOOK ON HIS FACE,
LIKE HE'D SEEN A GHOST.
HE MUST HAVE BUMPED INTO THE GUY
YESTERDAY DURING THE PRELIMS.
I BET THAT'S WHEN HE REALIZED
SOMEONE FROM LAUGHING COFFIN
WAS IN "G. G. O.,"
SOMEONE WHO FIGURED OUT HOW
TO KILL PLAYERS FOR REAL AGAIN.
MY BROTHER WENT BACK
TO PUT AN END TO THAT NIGHTMARE,
TO FIND OUT HIS NAME, AND STOP
HIS P.K.ING ONCE AND FOR ALL.
Asuna: (THINKING)
DARN IT, KIRITO.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SAID SOMETHING.
WHY? WHY DO YOU ALWAYS DO THIS?
Kirito: THAT DAMN IDIOT!
WHY DIDN'T HE SAY ANYTHING?
I COULD BE
BACKING HIM UP RIGHT NOW,
ALL HE HAD TO DO WAS ASK, AND I
WOULD HAVE CONVERTED OVER, TOO.
Silica: WE ALL WOULD HAVE.
DON'T YOU SEE?
THAT'S WHY HE DIDN'T TELL US.
IF HE THOUGHT THERE WAS ANY REAL
DANGER IN WHAT HE WAS DOING,
THERE'S NO WAY
HE'D GET US MIXED UP IN IT, TOO.
THAT'S JUST HOW HE IS.
Lisbeth: YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE ALWAYS THINKS OF OTHERS
BEFORE HIMSELF.
IN FACT, HE'S PROBABLY
PROTECTING SOMEONE RIGHT NOW,
AND WHOEVER THAT IS,
I BET IT'S SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T LIKE HIM MUCH.
Asuna: OKAY, CHRYSHEIGHT,
WHERE IS KIRITO DIVING FROM?
I KNOW YOU KNOW,
SO YOU BETTER TELL ME NOW.
Kikuoka: MM...
THAT'S CONFIDENTIAL.
EH, OKAY, OKAY. I'LL TELL YOU.
I SET UP THE ROOM MYSELF,
SO HE'S SAFE.
SECURITY'S ROCK‐SOLID,
AND THE MONITORING'S
TOP OF THE LINE.
I'VE GOT A TRAINED PROFESSIONAL
RIGHT BY HIS SIDE AT ALL TIMES,
AND I GUARANTEE THAT HIS BODY'S
IN NO DANGER WHATSOEVER.
Asuna: WHERE IS HE?!
Kikuoka: A HOSPITAL.
IT'S IN OCHANOMIZU
IN CHIYODA WARD.
Asuna: HE'S IN CHIYODA?
WAIT. IS THAT THE SAME HOSPITAL
HE WAS IN
DURING HIS REHABILITATION?
Kikuoka: YES, THAT'S THE ONE.
Asuna: I'M GOING OVER THERE.
I WANT TO SEE HIM,
AND YOU CAN'T DO
A THING ABOUT IT.
Sinon: TELL ME YOU GOT A PLAN.
Kirito: WE'RE GOING
TO TAKE OUT DEATH GUN.
ONCE WE DO,
HIS REAL WORLD PARTNER'LL
STAND DOWN.
THEN HE'LL JUST LEAVE
YOUR APARTMENT.
Sinon: OKAY, BUT HE'S SKILLED,
BLACK STAR OR NO BLACK STAR.
YOU SAW.
HE DODGED HECATE'S BULLET
FROM JUST 100 METERS AWAY.
AND BESIDES, I CAN'T HIDE
IN THIS CAVE FOREVER, YOU KNOW.
BY NOW, THE OTHER PLAYERS
PROBABLY FIGURED OUT
THE TWO OF US ARE IN HERE.
WE MIGHT AS WELL
BE SITTING DUCKS.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SOMEONE
TOSSES A GRENADE IN.
Kirito: YOU'RE RIGHT.
Sinon: WE'VE BEEN A TEAM
THIS WHOLE TIME ANYWAY, RIGHT?
MIGHT AS WELL
FINISH IT TOGETHER.
Kirito: OKAY,
BUT THERE'S STILL THE RISK
HE SHOOTS YOU WITH THAT GUN.
Sinon: OH, THAT THING.
IT'S JUST AN OLD‐SCHOOL
SINGLE‐ACTION SIDEARM.
HE CAN FIRE IT ALL HE WANTS,
BUT I GOT YOU THERE.
JUST DEFLECT THE BULLETS
WITH YOUR SWORD.
Kirito: RIGHT, AND I WON'T LET
A SINGLE ONE OF 'EM HIT YOU.
I STILL DON'T FEEL GOOD
ABOUT YOU BEING
OUT THERE, THOUGH.
I MEAN, DEATH GUN'S DANGEROUS,
AND YOU SHOULDN'T GET
TOO CLOSE TO HIM.
Sinon: OH, COME ON.
Kirito: HANG ON.
I'M TOTALLY COOL
WITH YOU FIGHTING WITH ME, AND I
WOULDN'T HAVE IT ANY OTHER WAY,
BUT, SINON,
YOU'RE A SNIPER, REMEMBER?
ISN'T YOUR SPECIALTY
THE LONG‐RANGE ATTACK?
Sinon: WELL, YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT IT?
Kirito: HERE'S THE PLAN.
ON THE NEXT SCAN,
I'M GONNA STEP OUTSIDE
SO IT PICKS ME UP.
THAT WAY, WE'LL GET
DEATH GUN TO COME TO US.
HE'LL PROBABLY KEEP HIS DISTANCE
AND TAKE COVER.
THEN HE'LL TRY TO PICK ME OFF
WITH HIS RIFLE.
WHEN HE SHOOTS,
WE'LL KNOW WHERE HE IS,
AND THEN YOU TAKE HIM OUT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
Sinon: ARE YOU COOL
WITH PLAYING THE DECOY?
Kirito: MM‐HMM.
Sinon: ALL RIGHT.
WE DO IT YOUR WAY THEN.
JUST BE CAREFUL OUT THERE,
'CAUSE IF HE DROPS YOU
WITH HIS FIRST SHOT,
I'M GONNA BE PISSED.
Kirito: HEH.
I'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
WAIT. I JUST REMEMBERED.
HIS RIFLE'S GOT A SILENCER,
AND YOU WON'T SEE
THE BULLET LINE
ON THE FIRST SHOT.
Sinon: OH, I'LL JUST PREDICT
THE PREDICTION,
YOU KNOW, LIKE A CERTAIN
NO‐GOOD FAKER TOLD‐‐
Kirito: UM, I THINK
WE SHOULD STOP TALKING.
Sinon: UH...
UGH. OH, CRAP.
WE SHOULD HAVE BEEN
PAYING MORE ATTENTION.
Kirito: WHAT IS IT?
AND WILL IT KILL US?
Sinon:
IT'S A LIVE‐STREAM CAMERA.
USUALLY THEY'RE
ONLY SUPPOSED TO SHADOW
PLAYERS ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
I GUESS THIS ONE'S
IN HERE NOW
'CAUSE THERE AREN'T
MANY OF US LEFT OUT THERE.
Kirito: THEN DO YOU...
THINK IT HEARD US?
Sinon: NOT A CHANCE.
FOR IT TO PICK US UP,
WE'D HAVE TO BE SHOUTING
AT THE TOP OF OUR LUNGS.
WAVE TO THE AUDIENCE.
UNLESS YOU GOT
SOMEONE BACK AT HOME
YOU DON'T WANT SEEING THIS.
Kirito: (GRUNTS)
UH, I, UM...
SHOULDN'T YOU BE WORRIED
WHO'S WATCHING?
I MEAN, SINCE I SORT OF
LOOK LIKE A GIRL,
THEY MIGHT, YOU KNOW,
THINK YOU'RE, YOU KNOW.
Sinon: I DON'T CARE.
THEY CAN THINK WHAT THEY WANT.
THE GUYS IN THIS GAME ARE DORKS.
IF THEY THINK I'M GAY,
AT LEAST THEY'LL STOP HITTING
ON ME EVERY FIVE SECONDS.
Kirito: HOW MUCH LONGER
AM I GONNA HAVE TO KEEP
PRETENDING TO BE A GIRL?
Sinon: OH, YOU POOR BABY.
YOU'VE BEEN FAKING IT LIKE
A CHAMP SINCE YOU LOGGED IN.
ANOTHER HOUR OR TWO
WON'T MATTER.
THANK GOD.
(SIGHS)
WE BETTER GET READY.
WE GOT TWO MINUTES
BEFORE THE NEXT SAT SCAN.
I'LL SET UP HERE.
WHEN YOU GET OUTSIDE,
FIRE UP YOUR TERMINAL,
AND LET ME KNOW
WHEN OUR BOY'S CLOSE.
Kirito: WAIT. HOLD ON.
Sinon: WHY? WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S TOO LATE
TO CHANGE THE PLAN NOW.
Kirito: NO, I DON'T WANT
TO CHANGE ANYTHING.
IT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT
DEATH GUN'S REAL HANDLE HERE.
THE ONLY NAME
YOU DIDN'T RECOGNIZE
WHO'S STILL ALIVE IS STERBEN.
Sinon: OH. HUH.
I GUESS THAT'S HIM THEN.
I WONDER WHY HE GAVE HIMSELF
THAT NAME, THOUGH.
Kirito: IF I GET
UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL,
I'LL BE SURE TO ASK HIM FOR YOU.
WELL, HERE GOES NOTHING.
Sinon: BE CAREFUL, OKAY?