Sinon: (PANTING)
(YELPS)
Kyoji: A‐ASADA!
Sinon: NO.
LET GO OF ME! NO!
Kyoji: ASADA. ASADA.
ASADA! ASADA!
‐ ASADA! ASADA!
‐ Sinon: (SCREAMS)
Kyoji: ASADA!
Sinon: (GASPS)
Both: (GRUNTING)
Kirito: RUN, SINON!
Sinon: KIRITO.
Both: (GRUNTING)
Kyoji: WHAT THE HELL?
GET OFF ME!
BASTARD! IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
SHE'S MINE.
SHE'S MINE, DAMN IT!
STAY AWAY FROM HER!
(LAUGHS)
Sinon: KIRITO!
(SYRINGE HISSES)
Sinon: (GASPS)
Kyoji: (CHUCKLING)
Sinon: KIRITO.
Kirito: HE GOT ME.
IT HAPPENED SO FAST.
DIDN'T EVEN SEE THE NEEDLE.
Sinon: I KNOW.
I'M GONNA TAKE A LOOK, OKAY?
Kirito: (GASPING)
Sinon: HANG ON.
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU
DIE LIKE THIS.
(GASPS)
Kirito: (SHUDDERING)
Sinon: UM, HEY...
YOU GOT THIS WEIRD THING
ON YOUR CHEST.
Kirito: PLEASE TELL ME
THAT'S WHERE HE HIT ME
WITH THE NEEDLE.
Sinon: IT LOOKS LIKE IT,
I GUESS.
WHAT IS THAT THING, ANYWAY?
Kirito: (SIGHS)
IT'S ONE OF THE ELECTRODES
FROM THIS HEART MONITOR
I WAS HOOKED UP TO.
Sinon: HEART MONITOR?
Kirito: NEVER MIND.
YOU KNOW, YOU SCARED
THE HELL OUT OF ME.
Sinon: I SCARED YOU?!
HOW DO YOU THINK I FEEL?!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA DIE
JUST NOW, YOU DUMB‐ASS!
Kirito: HEY! EASY!
(SIGHS)
Sinon: (SIGHS)
MM.
Kirito: HE'S NOT DEAD, IS HE?
Sinon: NAH,
HE'S STILL GOT A PULSE.
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE CRAZY,
BUT THANK YOU FOR COMING OVER.
Kirito: NO, THANK YOU
FOR CLOCKING HIM WHEN YOU DID.
I'M SORRY
I COULDN'T GET HERE SOONER.
UH, YOU OKAY?
Sinon: MM‐HMM.
(CRYING)
Girls: (CHATTERING, LAUGHING)
Girl: I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
THE LOOK ON HER FACE.
Girl #2: RIGHT.
(LAUGHING STOPS)
Sinon: NEXT TIME YOU WANNA MEET,
BE ON TIME.
Girl #1: SERIOUSLY?
GIRL, YOU BEEN ACTING
WAY TOO COCKY LATELY.
Girl #2: SHE'S RIGHT.
WE SHOULD TEACH YOU A LESSON.
Endo: NAH, YOU GUYS.
IT'S COOL.
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS HERE, RIGHT?
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE FRIENDS.
THEY COME IN REAL HANDY,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU NEED A LOAN.
Girls: (CHUCKLE)
Endo: SPEAKING OF,
I NEED 20K, BUDDY.
Sinon: I TOLD YOU BEFORE.
I'M NOT LENDING YOU GUYS
ANY MONEY.
Endo: YOU'LL CHANGE YOUR MIND
AFTER I SHOW YOU
WHAT MY BROTHER GAVE ME.
Sinon: I DOUBT IT.
Endo: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: (GASPS)
Endo: GET THIS. HE TOLD ME
NOT TO POINT THIS AT ANYONE,
BUT WHAT DOES HE KNOW?
I MEAN, YOU'VE SEEN ONE BEFORE,
SO IT DOESN'T BUG YOU, RIGHT?
OR DOES IT, ASADA?
GET ON YOUR KNEES,
AND SAY YOU'RE SORRY.
‐ Sinon: (GASPING)
‐ (HEART BEATING)
Endo: (CHUCKLES)
‐ WAAH!
Endo: CRAP. IT'S NOT WORKING.
OW!
Sinon: GOVERNMENT‐ISSUE M1911.
YOUR BROTHER HAS GOOD TASTE.
IT'S NOT REALLY
MY STYLE, THOUGH.
AND FOR FUTURE REFERENCE,
IT ONLY FIRES
WHEN THE SAFETY'S OFF.
Girls: (GASPING)
Sinon: (INHALES)
Endo: HEY, WHOA.
Sinon: YOUR BROTHER'S RIGHT.
YOU SHOULDN'T POINT THIS
AT PEOPLE.
HERE.
‐ OH, MY GOD. ARE YOU OKAY?
‐ COME ON. GET UP, ENDO.
Sinon: SEE YOU AROUND.
(GASPING)
THEY SAY THE FIRST STEP'S
ALWAYS THE HARDEST.
(GIRLS MURMURING)
Sinon: HUH?
(GASPS)
Girl #3: HEY, ASADA,
DO YOU KNOW THAT GUY?
Girl #4: IS HE YOUR BOYFRIEND?
‐ AWW.
Sinon: REALLY?
WHEN I SAID I'D MEET YOU,
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D PARK
YOURSELF IN FRONT OF MY SCHOOL.
Kirito: HMM?
OH, WHAT'S UP, SINON?
Sinon: (SIGHS)
Kirito: KYOJI SHINKAWA
AND HIS OLDER BROTHER SHOICHI
WERE ARRESTED.
DURING THE INTERROGATION,
IT CAME OUT THAT ANOTHER PERSON
WAS INVOLVED.
THIS THIRD DEATH GUN,
ATSUSHI KANAMOTO,
IS STILL OUT THERE,
BUT KIKUOKA SAYS
THEY'LL CATCH HIM SOON ENOUGH.
THEY GOT THE IDEA OF CREATING
THE DEATH GUN CHARACTER
WHEN SHOICHI GOT
THE INVISIBILITY CLOAK
THROUGH A REAL‐MONEY TRADE.
USING THE CLOAK
AND SOME BINOCULARS,
SHOICHI STARTED STEALING
THE REAL‐WORLD INFO
OF THE OTHER PLAYERS.
MEANWHILE,
HIS LITTLE BROTHER KYOJI
WAS HAVING ISSUES
WITH HIS AVATAR, SPIEGEL.
ZXE‐D: THESE PLAYERS WHO THINK
IT'S ALL ABOUT
THEIR AGILITY‐‐HEH‐‐
MAN, THEY'RE LIVING IN A DREAM.
Kirito: SPIEGEL WAS AN AGI‐TYPE,
WHICH ZXE‐D USED TO RECOMMEND,
BUT ZXE‐D SHIFTED HIS STATS
TO A STR‐VIT COMBO,
AND THAT PISSED KYOJI OFF.
WHEN SHOICHI FOUND OUT,
HE GAVE KYOJI ZXE‐D's NAME
AND ADDRESS I. R. L.
THEN THEY STARTED TALKING
ABOUT HOW TO KILL HIM.
THEY SAY THEY WEREN'T
SERIOUS ABOUT IT AT FIRST,
BUT DAY AFTER DAY,
THE MORE THEY TALKED ABOUT IT,
THE MORE IT SEEMED
THEY COULD GET AWAY WITH IT.
FOR THEIR PLAN TO WORK,
THEY NEEDED TWO THINGS
FROM THEIR DAD'S HOSPITAL,
A MASTER KEY CARD USED
TO OPEN DOORS IN EMERGENCIES
AND A LETHAL DRUG FOR THE DEED.
THEY RESEARCHED
THEIR VICTIMS CAREFULLY,
NARROWING THE LIST DOWN
TO THE ONES WHO LIVED ALONE
IN LOW‐SECURITY APARTMENTS.
USING THE KEY CARD,
SHOICHI BROKE INTO
THEIR FIRST VICTIM'S PLACE,
SHIGEMURA, A. K. A. ZXE‐D.
THE BROTHERS WORKED OUT
THE EXACT TIME
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO DIE,
WHEN KYOJI LOGGED IN
AS HIS BROTHER'S AVATAR STERBEN
AND ANNOUNCED HIMSELF
AS DEATH GUN AND SHOT ZXE‐D.
THEIR SECOND VICTIM,
USUSHIO TARAKO,
WAS KILLED THE SAME WAY.
BUT INSTEAD OF BEING SCARED
OF DEATH GUN,
THE OTHER PLAYERS IN "GGO"
TREATED IT
LIKE SOME KIND OF JOKE.
Kirito: SHOICHI AND HIS PARTNERS
WERE FURIOUS,
SO THEY DECIDED
TO KILL SOME PLAYERS
DURING THE B. o. B FINAL.
THEY FOUND THREE
WHO MET THE SAME CRITERIA
AS ZXE‐D AND TARAKO‐‐
PALE RIDER, GARRETT, AND SINON.
KILLING THREE PEOPLE WAS
GONNA MAKE THINGS HARD
FOR JUST THE TWO OF THEM,
THOUGH.
Kikuoka: YEAH.
TO BE IN SYNC WITH DEATH GUN,
THE PERSON DOING
THE REAL‐WORLD KILLING
HAD TO MAKE SURE THEY'D BE
AT EACH TARGET'S HOUSE ON TIME.
Kirito: SO THEY RECRUITED THAT
KANAMOTO GUY YOU TOLD ME ABOUT
TO BE THE THIRD DEATH GUN.
WHERE'D THEY FIND HIM, THOUGH?
Kikuoka: SIMPLE. KANAMOTO WAS
AN OLD FRIEND OF SHOICHI'S.
THEY WERE BOTH PART
OF LAUGHING COFFIN IN "S. A. O."
WE FOUND OUT HIS HANDLE THERE
WAS JOHNNY BLACK.
THAT SOUND FAMILIAR?
Kirito: YEAH.
HE WORKED WITH XAXA.
I THINK HIS WEAPON OF CHOICE
WAS A POISON KNIFE.
Kikuoka: THEY PUT KANAMOTO
ON PALE RIDER AND GARRETT,
'CAUSE HE LIVED NEARBY.
SINON, ON THE OTHER HAND,
WAS KYOJI'S.
SEE, SHOICHI WAS THE ONE
WHO USUALLY DID THE KILLING,
BUT FOR THIS ONE JOB,
KYOJI INSISTED ON BEING
THE ONE TO DO IT.
‐ Sinon: UM...
‐ Kikuoka: HMM?
Sinon: IS THAT
WHAT HE WANTED FOR REAL?
DID SHINKA‐‐
I MEAN KYOJI SAY THAT?
Kikuoka: NO.
HIS BROTHER WAS THE ONE
WHO GAVE US
ALL THE DETAILS OF THEIR PLAN.
KYOJI STILL REFUSES TO TALK.
Sinon: HE DOES, HUH?
Kikuoka: SPEAKING OF,
WE FOUND OUT
A LITTLE MORE ABOUT SHOICHI.
HEALTHWISE, HE'D BEEN
SICKLY SINCE CHILDHOOD.
HIS FATHER PRETTY MUCH
GAVE UP ON HIM,
SO HE DECIDED EARLY ON
TO HAND THE HOSPITAL OVER
TO KYOJI.
Kyoji: STAYING SHARP, MA'AM,
LOCKED AND LOADED.
Kikuoka: EVEN SO, THE BROTHERS
SEEMED TO BE CLOSE GROWING UP,
BUT THEN SHOICHI
GOT OBSESSED WITH MMORPGs,
AND IN 2022, HE GOT TRAPPED
IN "SWORD ART ONLINE."
AFTER HE GOT OUT,
SHOICHI ONLY SPOKE
TO KYOJI ABOUT IT.
HE BRAGGED ABOUT HOW,
IN THAT WORLD,
HE WAS A REAL MASS MURDERER
AND HOW HE WAS FEARED.
IN KYOJI'S EYES,
HIS BIG BROTHER WAS A HERO.
AS FOR SHOICHI,
HE'S STICKING WITH THE STORY
THAT EVERYTHING
ABOUT THE DEATH GUN CONCEPT,
INCLUDING THE MURDERS,
WAS JUST PART OF A GAME,
THAT HIS ACTIONS HERE,
LIKE GATHERING INTEL ON VICTIMS,
PREPPING FOR THE MURDERS,
AND COMMITTING THEM, WERE
NO DIFFERENT THAN IN "S. A. O."
Kirito: THE DARK SIDE OF VRMMOs,
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
HIS REALITY GOT A LOT LESS REAL.
Kikuoka: YEAH. GOOD POINT.
AND HOW ARE YOU HANDLING YOURS?
Kirito: I FEEL LIKE I LEFT
A PART OF ME BACK IN "S. A. O.,"
SO RIGHT NOW, THERE'S LESS OF ME
HERE THAN THERE WAS BEFORE.
I DON'T KNOW.
Kikuoka: YOU DON'T KNOW?
DO YOU WANNA GO BACK?
Kirito: SERIOUSLY?
HOW COULD YOU ASK ME THAT?
Sinon: UM, WAIT A SEC.
YOU'RE KIND OF CONTRADICTING
WHAT YOU TOLD ME THE OTHER DAY.
Kirito: WHAT?
Sinon: YOU SAID
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS A VIRTUAL WORLD, REMEMBER?
THAT, LIKE, WHEREVER YOU WERE,
THAT'S YOUR REALITY.
WHERE I AM RIGHT NOW, HERE,
THIS WORLD IS MY REALITY.
AND EVEN IF YOU TOLD ME
THIS WAS A VIRTUAL WORLD,
IT WOULD STILL BE REALITY TO ME.
YOU SEE WHAT I MEAN?
Kirito: I GUESS.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU, SINON.
WHAT YOU SAID JUST NOW
MIGHT BE THE ONLY GOOD THING
TO COME OUT OF THIS NIGHTMARE.
Sinon: OH, PUT A SOCK IN IT.
Kikuoka: SORRY,
I'M WITH KIRITO ON THIS ONE.
WELL, I TOLD YOU PRETTY MUCH
ALL WE'VE FOUND OUT SO FAR.
YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
BEFORE I GO?
Sinon: I DO.
HAS THERE BEEN ANY WORD
ON WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
TO KYOJI YET?
Kikuoka: BASED ON HIS BROTHER'S
CONFESSION AND THEIR BEHAVIOR,
THEY'LL MOST LIKELY BE SENT
TO A MEDICAL DETENTION CENTER.
I DOUBT EITHER ONE KNOWS
WHAT REALITY IS ANYMORE.
Sinon: NO,
I DON'T THINK THAT'S TRUE.
Kikuoka: HMM?
Sinon: I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT KYOJI'S BROTHER.
I NEVER MET HIM.
BUT I'VE KNOWN KYOJI
A LONG TIME,
AND, WELL, I THINK HIS REALITY
WAS "GUN GALE ONLINE."
HE HAD PRETTY MUCH GIVEN UP
ON THIS WORLD.
THERE WAS NOTHING LEFT FOR HIM
OTHER THAN "GGO,"
SO HE MADE THAT HIS REALITY.
HE'D SPEND HOURS IN IT
GRINDING AWAY,
BOOSTING HIS XP,
AND TRYING TO BE THE BEST.
I GUESS THE STRESS
GOT TO BE TOO MUCH FOR HIM.
Kikuoka: FROM PLAYING A GAME?
I KNOW YOU CAN LOSE TRACK
OF TIME, BUT REALITY?
Sinon: SURE. AT SOME POINT,
KYOJI JUST SWAPPED OUT
ONE FOR THE OTHER,
HIS REAL LIFE
FOR HIS VIRTUAL ONE.
Kikuoka: OKAY, BUT WHY?
Sinon: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I WISH I DID.
KIRITO, WHY DO YOU
THINK HE DID IT?
Kirito: TO GET STRONGER.
Sinon: YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GUESS I WAS THE SAME WAY.
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
MAYBE ALL US VRMMO PLAYERS
ARE THE SAME.
ALL WE WANT IS TO GET STRONGER.
MR. KIKUOKA,
I'D LIKE TO GO SEE HIM
IF THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S SO MUCH
I WANT TO TELL HIM,
LIKE WHAT WE WERE
JUST TALKING ABOUT
AND OTHER STUFF I'VE
BEEN THINKING, IF IT'S OKAY.
Kikuoka: MM. YOU'RE
A STRONG PERSON TO WANT TO,
AND I, FOR ONE,
THINK IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
HE CAN'T HAVE VISITORS YET,
BUT WHEN HE CAN,
I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
WELL, I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO THE OFFICE NOW.
Kirito: OKAY.
THANKS FOR TAKING THE TIME.
Sinon: YES, THANK YOU
FOR TALKING TO US.
Kikuoka: DON'T EVEN MENTION IT.
YOU GUYS RISKED YOUR LIVES,
AND GOD KNOWS
HOW MANY YOU SAVED.
IT'S THE LEAST I COULD DO.
OH, BY THE WAY, KIRITO,
DEATH GUN OR SHOICHI SHINKAWA
OR RED‐EYED XAXA
OR WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL HIM
ASKED ME TO GIVE YOU A MESSAGE.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT,
SAY THE WORD,
AND I'LL TEAR IT UP.
Kirito: I'LL HEAR IT.
Kikuoka: YOU GOT IT.
HE WROTE,
"IF YOU THINK THIS IS OVER,
IT'S NOT.
YOU DON'T HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES TO END THIS.
SOONER OR LATER,
YOU'LL REALIZE THAT.
IT'S SHOWTIME."
THAT'S IT.
Kirito: HEY, UH, SINON.
Sinon: HMM? WHAT'S UP?
Kirito: ARE YOU FREE RIGHT NOW?
Sinon: WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "FREE"?
FREE FOR WHAT?
(MOTORCYCLE REVS)
SO THIS IS WHERE
YOU'RE TAKING ME?
Kirito: YEP. THERE'S SOMEONE
INSIDE I WANT YOU TO MEET.
Lisbeth: WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME.
YOU MADE US WAIT SO DARN LONG,
I WENT AND HAD
TWO SLICES OF APPLE PIE.
IF I GET FAT,
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
Kirito: HOW'S THAT
MY FAULT? JEEZ.
Asuna: COME ON, KIRITO.
ARE YOU GONNA INTRODUCE US
OR WHAT?
Kirito: HUH? OH, RIGHT. SORRY.
THIS IS SHINO ASADA,
A. K. A. SINON,
"GUN GALE ONLINE'S"
THIRD SUPER‐CHAMP.
Sinon: OH, DON'T SAY THAT.
Lisbeth: (GROANS)
Kirito: (CLEARS THROAT)
THESE ARE MY FRIENDS
FROM MY TIME IN "S. A. O.,"
RIKA, A. K. A. LIZ,
BLACKSMITH AND SWINDLER.
Lisbeth: HUH?
WHAT THE HELL'D YOU CALL ME?
HAH! (GROANS)
Kirito: AND THAT'S ASUNA,
THE BERSERK HEALER,
REAL NAME ASUNA YUUKI.
Asuna: UH, BERSERK?
‐ Lisbeth: (GROANS)
‐ Sinon: UH...
Kirito: YOU WANNA GRAB A SEAT
AND GET SOMETHING TO DRINK?
Sinon: THAT'S WHAT STER‐‐
I MEAN SCHTERBEN MEANS,
A TERM HOSPITALS USE FOR DEATH.
WHAT WAS HE THINKING GIVING
HIS AVATAR A NAME LIKE THAT?
Asuna: IF I WERE YOU,
I WOULDN'T TRY TO FIND
SOME DEEPER MEANING IN THE NAME
HE GAVE HIS AVATAR.
A LOT OF TIMES, IT BOILS DOWN
TO WHATEVER A PLAYER
THINKS SOUND COOL.
Lisbeth: OH, THAT EXPLAINS IT.
THIS WHOLE TIME, I THOUGHT
YOU GAVE YOUR AVATAR YOUR NAME
'CAUSE YOU LACKED IMAGINATION.
‐ Asuna: ZIP IT.
‐ Lisbeth: AHH.
Asuna: I DO SO HAVE IMAGINATION,
LOTS OF IT.
Lisbeth: OKAY! JEEZ.
‐ Asuna: WHATEVER.
‐ Lisbeth: (GIGGLES)
Asuna: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: (SIGHS)
Lisbeth: SO ANYWAY,
I'M SUPER STOKED YOU'RE HERE.
IT'S ALWAYS COOL TO MEET
ANOTHER GIRL VRMMO PLAYER.
Asuna: YOU SAID IT.
I HOPE WE CAN BE
GREAT FRIENDS, ASADA.
Sinon: (GASPS)
Asuna: HMM.
LISTEN, ASADA, SHINO,
THERE'S ANOTHER REASON FOR US
ASKING YOU TO COME HERE TODAY.
Sinon: WHAT IS IT?
Kirito: SINON, I'M SORRY
TO PUT YOU
ON THE SPOT LIKE THIS.
I, UH‐‐I TOLD ASUNA AND LIZ
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNGER.
Sinon: (GASPS)
Kirito: I DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE.
I NEEDED THEIR HELP.
Sinon: HUH?
Asuna: I'LL EXPLAIN.
WE WANTED TO HELP YOU,
SO WE PAID A VISIT TO THE TOWN
WHERE YOU USED TO LIVE.
Sinon: (GASPS)
HOW COULD YOU?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
Kirito: WAIT, SINON.
THEY FOUND SOMEONE
WHO WANTS TO MEET YOU.
I CAN'T LET YOU LEAVE TILL YOU
HEAR WHAT THEY HAVE TO SAY.
IT MIGHT HURT, AND I'M SORRY,
BUT I CAN'T STAND BY
IF THERE'S A CHANCE
WHAT THEY SAY HELPS.
Sinon: WHO IS THIS PERSON?
WHAT DO THEY WANT TO TELL ME?
SORRY. DO I KNOW YOU?
Sachie: SACHIE OOSAWA.
YOU'RE SHINO ASADA, AREN'T YOU?
I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO MY DAUGHTER.
HER NAME'S MIZUEH.
SHE'S FOUR YEARS OLD.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU REMEMBER,
BUT I USED TO WORK
AT THE POST OFFICE.
Sinon: (GASPS)
Sachie: (GASPS)
Sachie: I'M SORRY.
THIS IS REALLY HARD.
SEE, I‐‐
I SHOULD HAVE
DONE THIS AGES AGO.
I'M SO SORRY IT TOOK THIS LONG.
I NEVER APOLOGIZED
OR THANKED YOU FOR WHAT YOU DID.
I WAS PREGNANT WITH HER
THE DAY THAT MAN CAME IN
AND TRIED TO ROB US.
WHAT YOU DID, IT WASN'T
JUST MY LIFE YOU SAVED.
YOU SAVED THE LIFE
OF MY LITTLE GIRL, TOO.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU,
SHE WOULDN'T BE HERE.
Sinon: I SAVED YOUR DAUGHTER?
Kirito: SINON, TIME TO LET GO.
YOU'VE BEEN BLAMING YOURSELF
WAY TOO LONG,
BEATING YOURSELF UP
OVER WHAT HAPPENED.
I'M NOT SAYING YOU'RE
WRONG TO DO THAT, BUT...
(INHALES)
IT'S JUST WHATEVER GUILT
YOU FEEL ABOUT WHAT YOU DID,
YOU GOT A RIGHT TO CONSIDER
THE LIVES YOU SAVED, TOO.
YOU GOT THE RIGHT
TO THINK ABOUT THOSE PEOPLE
AND FORGIVE YOURSELF.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S WHAT
I WANTED YOU TO KNOW.
(STOOL THUMPS)
Mizueh: I MADE IT FOR YOU.
THANK YOU FOR SAVING MOMMY
AND FOR SAVING ME.
WE LOVE YOU. (GIGGLES)
(GIGGLES)
Sinon: (CHUCKLES)