Sinon: (GASPS)
A TYPE 54 BLACK STAR.
IT'S THE GUN.
WHY?
WHY HERE?
WHY DOES HE HAVE THAT GUN?
(HEART BEATING)
(WHIMPERS)
(GASPING)
Robber: (LAUGHS)
Sinon: WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE STRONG,
TO BE BRAVE...
I THOUGHT SOMEHOW I COULD
LEARN THOSE THINGS FROM KIRITO.
I DON'T WANNA DIE.
(GUNSHOT ECHOES)
(BULLET WHIZZES)
A GRENADE.
KIRI...TO.
I'M SLOWING YOU DOWN.
JUST LEAVE ME.
NOT THE HORSE.
IT CAN GO FAST,
BUT IT'S TOO HARD TO HANDLE.
Kirito: SINON, GET YOUR RIFLE,
AND BLOW THAT HORSE AWAY.
Sinon: HUH? WHAT?
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TRY.
(HEART BEATING)
(GASPS)
NO. MY FINGER.
I CAN'T PULL IT.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T PULL THE TRIGGER.
(GASPS)
Kirito: HANG ON TIGHT.
Robber: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: (SIGHS) IT'S NO USE.
Kirito: WE CAN STILL GET AWAY.
STAY SHARP, DAMN IT.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Sinon: NO.
HE'S CATCHING UP.
HURRY! FASTER!
PLEASE DON'T LET HIM
CATCH UP TO US.
(WHIMPERING)
(GASPS)
(YELPS)
HELP ME. I CAN'T DO THIS.
I DON'T WANNA DIE!
Kirito: HEY, SINON,
SNAP OUT OF IT!
LISTEN,
HE'S CATCHING UP WITH US.
PICK UP YOUR GUN, AND SHOOT HIM!
Sinon: NO, I CAN'T.
Kirito: YOU DON'T
HAVE TO HIT HIM.
JUST DISTRACT HIM.
Sinon: I CAN'T!
DON'T MAKE ME. DON'T MAKE ME.
Kirito: THEN GET UP HERE,
AND STEER THIS THING.
GIVE ME YOUR GUN,
AND I'LL SHOOT HIM.
Sinon: HECATE.
SHE'S PART OF ME.
I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN USE HER.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T SHOOT.
I CAN'T MOVE MY FINGER.
I CAN'T. I CAN'T FIGHT ANYMORE.
Kirito: YOU CAN!
EVERYONE CAN FIGHT
IF THEY WANT TO.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE,
SO WHAT'LL IT BE?
WILL YOU GIVE UP,
OR WILL YOU FIGHT?
Sinon: IF IT'S MY CHOICE,
THEN I DON'T WANT
TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
I'M DONE.
I DON'T WANT TO SUFFER ANYMORE.
I THOUGHT I COULD GET STRONGER
PLAYING THIS GAME,
BUT I WAS WRONG.
(GASPS)
Kirito: I'LL HELP YOU,
BUT YOU HAVE TO TRY,
SO COME ON. YOU CAN DO THIS.
(HEART BEATING)
Sinon: IT'S NO GOOD.
WITH ALL THIS SHAKING AROUND,
I CAN'T LOCK ON.
Kirito: IT'S OKAY. THE SHAKING'S
GONNA STOP IN THREE,
TWO, ONE,
NOW!
Sinon: HOW'S HE DO IT?
HOW CAN HE BE SO CALM NOW?
NO, IT'S NOT
THAT HE'S BEING CALM.
HE'S GIVING IT
EVERYTHING HE'S GOT.
WHEN HE FIGHTS,
HE GOES ALL OUT EVERY TIME,
NO EXCUSES.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S WHERE
HE GETS HIS STRENGTH.
I MISSED.
Kirito: THIS ISN'T GOOD.
WE'RE LIKE SITTING DUCKS
OUT HERE.
WE NEED TO FIND SOME COVER.
Sinon: HEY, I THINK
I SEE A CAVE OVER THERE.
IF WE HIDE INSIDE,
WE CAN AVOID THE SAT SCAN.
Kirito: SOUNDS GOOD. LET'S GO.
(GROANS)
THIS IS PERFECT.
WE CAN DODGE THE SCAN
AND REST UP, TOO.
WHAT HAPPENED BACK THERE?
IT'S LIKE HE JUST POPPED UP
OUT OF NOWHERE.
WE DIDN'T SEE HIM ON THE SCAN.
THAT MUST MEAN HE'S GOT
SOME KIND OF CLOAKING SKILL.
IS THERE A SKILL LIKE THAT HERE,
INVISIBILITY?
Sinon: YEAH, THERE IS.
IT'S A SKILL
CALLED META‐MATERIAL
OPTICAL CAMOUFLAGE.
WE'RE SAFE, FOR NOW ANYWAY.
EVEN IF HE'S INVISIBLE,
THE SANDS ARE ROUGH HERE.
WE'LL HEAR IT CRUNCHING
UNDER HIS BOOTS.
WE'LL SEE
HIS FOOTPRINTS, TOO,
SO HE CAN'T SNEAK UP
LIKE HE DID BEFORE.
Kirito: ROGER THAT.
WELL, I GUESS WE'LL KEEP
OUR EYES AND EARS OPEN.
Sinon: HEY, KIRITO,
DO YOU THINK THERE'S A CHANCE
DEATH GUN WAS KILLED
IN THAT EXPLOSION?
Kirito: NO.
THE SECOND
BEFORE THAT TRUCK BLEW UP,
I SAW HIM JUMP
OFF OF THAT ROBOT HORSE.
HE MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN DINGED UP,
BUT I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT BLAST KILLED HIM.
Sinon: OH.
WHEN HE HAD ME IN HIS SIGHTS
BACK AT THE STADIUM,
I THOUGHT I WAS A GONER.
HOW'D YOU KNOW I WAS IN TROUBLE?
AND HOW'D YOU GET TO ME
SO FAST FROM YOUR POSITION?
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
WE WERE WRONG
ABOUT JUSHI X BEING DEATH GUN.
I TOOK ONE LOOK,
AND I KNEW IT WASN'T.
IT WAS PRETTY OBVIOUS, ACTUALLY.
Sinon: OBVIOUS?
Kirito: YEAH. I KNOW
A WOMAN WHEN I SEE ONE.
Sinon: OH.
Kirito: THE SECOND I SAW HER,
I KNEW WE OVERLOOKED SOMETHING.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT, THOUGH.
OH, BY THE WAY,
EVEN THOUGH
HER HANDLE SAYS JUSHI,
SHE CALLS HERSELF MUSKETEER X.
ANYWAY, AFTER I TOOK OUT
MUSKETEER X,
I LOOKED OVER TO THE SOUTH
AND SAW YOU LYING THERE
IN THE STREET.
I KNEW YOU WERE IN TROUBLE,
SO I GRABBED HER RIFLE
AND GRENADES AND CHARGED IN,
SHOOTING AND TOSSING BOMBS
AS FAST AS I COULD.
Sinon: I CAN'T BELIEVE
I LET MY GUARD DOWN LIKE THAT.
Kirito: DON'T GO
BEATING YOURSELF UP OVER IT.
I MEAN, LOOK,
IT'S NOT LIKE I KNEW
HE WAS HIDING DOWN THERE EITHER,
AND IF OUR ROLES WERE FLIPPED,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WOULD HAVE BEEN THE ONE
GETTING SHOT INSTEAD.
BUT THAT'S OKAY, 'CAUSE I KNOW
YOU WOULD HAVE RESCUED ME,
TOO, WOULDN'T YOU?
Sinon: (THINKING)
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
MY RIVAL'S TRYING
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
HE KNOWS I'M WEAK,
AND HERE HE IS CONSOLING ME,
LIKE I'M A KID OR SOMETHING.
Kirito: I'M HEADING OUT
FOR A BIT.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL KICK BACK HERE
AND REST UP WHILE YOU CAN.
I WISH YOU COULD LOG OUT,
BUT I KNOW YOU CAN'T,
NOT TILL THE TOURNEY'S OVER,
ANYWAY.
Sinon: HUH?
YOU'RE GOING AFTER DEATH GUN,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU THINK YOU CAN
TAKE HIM ON ALONE?
Kirito: YEAH. I HAVE TO.
HE'S TOUGH, AND HE WON'T GO DOWN
WITHOUT GETTING OFF
A SHOT OR TWO AT ME.
IF IT COMES DOWN TO THAT,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'LL DO.
I MIGHT BAIL.
I DON'T WANNA LEAVE YOU
HANGING LIKE THAT,
SO IT'S BETTER
IF I FACE HIM ALONE.
Sinon: THEN YOU'RE
SCARED OF HIM, TOO?
Kirito: YEAH, I AM.
IF IT WAS THE OLD ME,
I WOULD HAVE JUMPED RIGHT IN
AND FOUGHT HIM,
EVEN IF THERE WAS A CHANCE
I WAS GONNA DIE,
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
THESE DAYS, THERE'S THINGS
I HAVE TO PROTECT.
I CAN'T DIE.
I DON'T WANT TO.
Sinon: THINGS YOU
HAVE TO PROTECT?
Kirito: YEAH,
IN THE VIRTUAL WORLD
AND THE REAL ONE, TOO.
Sinon: OKAY.
THEN DON'T GO AFTER HIM.
JUST STAY HERE, AND KEEP LOW.
AS LONG AS B. o. B.'S GOING ON,
WE CAN'T LOG OUT,
BUT ONCE THE COMPETITION'S
WHITTLED DOWN TO US
AND ONE OTHER PLAYER,
WE CAN SUICIDE OUT
AND LET THE OTHER GUY WIN.
THAT'LL END THE TOURNAMENT.
Kirito: YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN,
THAT'S ONE WAY OF DOING IT.
THING IS, IT'S NOT REALLY
A GOOD OPTION.
IF WE JUST SIT HERE
AND WAIT FOR THE TOURNEY TO END,
THERE'S NO TELLING
HOW MANY OTHER PLAYERS
THAT GUY'S GONNA KILL.
Sinon: YEAH.
(THINKING) YOU REALLY
ARE STRONG AFTER ALL.
I'M NOT GONNA HIDE EITHER.
Kirito: HUH?
Sinon: I'M GOING OUTSIDE
AND HELP YOU
TAKE THAT BASTARD OUT.
Kirito: NO, YOU'RE NOT.
HAVEN'T YOU BEEN LISTENING?
IF HE SHOOTS YOU,
THERE'S A CHANCE YOU'LL DIE.
AS A PLAYER,
CLOSE COMBAT'S MY SPECIALTY.
IT'S NOT YOURS.
YOU'RE IN WAY MORE DANGER
THAN ME,
'CAUSE HE CAN BE
INVISIBLE IF HE WANTS.
HE'LL POP UP NEXT TO YOU,
AND BANG.
Sinon: I DON'T CARE IF I DIE.
Kirito: (GASPS)
Sinon: I WAS SCARED
OUT OF MY MIND
BACK AT THE STADIUM.
I WAS SCARED I WAS GONNA DIE.
I WAS EVEN WEAKER
THAN I WAS FIVE YEARS AGO,
LIKE A SCREAMING,
CRYING LITTLE GIRL.
IF THAT'S HOW I'M GONNA BE
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
I'D RATHER BE DEAD.
Kirito: IT'S ONLY NATURAL
TO BE AFRAID.
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE
WHO'S NOT AFRAID OF DYING.
Sinon: YEAH, WELL, I HATE IT.
I'M TIRED OF BEING AFRAID.
I'M SO TIRED.
WHATEVER.
I'M NOT ASKING TO GO WITH YOU.
I'LL FIGHT BY MYSELF.
Kirito: YOU WANT TO FIGHT ALONE
AND DIE ALONE.
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
Sinon: YEAH.
I WAS ALWAYS
SUPPOSED TO DIE ALONE.
(GRUNTS) LET GO.
I HAVE TO DO THIS.
Kirito: YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG.
THERE'S NO DYING ALONE.
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
WHEN YOU DIE, YOU LEAVE A HOLE
IN ALL THE PEOPLE
WHOSE LIVES YOU WERE PART OF,
AND LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOU'RE PART OF MINE NOW.
Sinon: YEAH, WELL, I NEVER
ASKED TO BE A PART OF IT.
BESIDES, MY LIFE'S
NO ONE ELSE'S BUSINESS BUT MINE.
Kirito: YOU'RE WRONG.
WE'RE INVOLVED
IN EACH OTHER'S LIVES NOW.
Sinon: (GASPS)
ALL RIGHT!
IF THAT'S HOW IT IS,
THEN YOU CAN PROTECT ME
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE!
(CRYING)
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING,
AND YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING,
SO DON'T GO SAYING
STUFF LIKE THAT!
THIS‐‐THIS ISN'T YOUR FIGHT!
IT'S MINE!
MINE! YOU GOT THAT?!
EVEN IF I LOSE, EVEN IF I DIE,
NO ONE CAN BLAME ME
FOR WHAT I DID.
YOU WANT TO HELP?
YOU GONNA CARRY
THIS BURDEN WITH ME?
THEN WHAT, HUH?
YOU GONNA HOLD MY HANDS
EVEN THOUGH THEY'VE
GOT BLOOD ALL OVER 'EM?!
Children: MURDERER.
MURDERER. MURDERER.
MURDERER.
Boy: MURDERER.
Girl: YOU MURDERER!
Second boy:
YOU KILL ANYONE TODAY?
First boy:
EWW. DON'T TOUCH ME.
YOU'LL GET ME ALL BLOODY.
Girl: WHY DON'T YOU
KILL YOURSELF?
Second boy: NYAH, NYAH!
First boy: PSYCHO!
(TAUNTING FADES)
Sinon: (CRYING)
I HATE YOU!
I HATE YOUR GUTS!
I HATE YOU.
(CONTINUES CRYING)
(WIND BLOWING)
EVEN THOUGH I HATE YOUR GUTS,
CAN I BORROW YOUR LAP FOR A SEC?
I...
I KILLED SOMEONE.
ABOUT FIVE YEARS AGO,
IN A SMALL TOWN UP NORTH,
THIS GUY TRIED TO ROB
A POST OFFICE.
THE NEWS SAID THE ROBBER DIED
'CAUSE HIS GUN
WENT OFF ACCIDENTALLY.
BUT THE TRUTH IS I WAS THERE.
I GRABBED HIS GUN
AND SHOT HIM DEAD.
Kirito: HOW OLD WERE YOU?
Sinon: 11 YEARS OLD.
AND EVER SINCE THEN,
WHENEVER I SEE A GUN,
I START THROWING UP,
AND THEN I PASS OUT.
IF I SEE A GUN,
I SEE THE FACE OF THE ROBBER
THE WAY HE LOOKED
RIGHT BEFORE HE DIED.
AND THEN I‐‐I GET SO SCARED.
Kirito: REALLY?
Sinon: YEAH, BUT IN THIS WORLD,
I DON'T HAVE THOSE PROBLEMS,
AND THAT GOT ME THINKING.
IF I CAN BECOME THE STRONGEST
PLAYER IN THE GAME,
THEN I'LL BE STRONG I. R. L., TOO,
AND MAYBE EVEN FORGET
WHAT I DID.
BUT JUST NOW‐‐
I MEAN, WHEN DEATH GUN
HAD ME PINNED,
I WAS TERRIFIED.
AND JUST LIKE THAT,
I WASN'T SINON ANYMORE.
I WAS THE REAL ME AGAIN.
I'M SCARED TO DIE. I AM.
ALTHOUGH, WHAT'S WORSE
IS LIVING WITH THIS FEAR.
IT'S SO PAINFUL,
I'D RATHER BE DEAD.
BUT I KNOW IF I RUN AWAY
FROM DEATH GUN AND MY PAST,
I'LL END UP WEAKER THAN BEFORE.
I WILL. I KNOW IT.
Kirito: YEAH.
I GET IT.
I KILLED SOMEONE ONCE, TOO.
Sinon: WHAT?
Kirito: I MENTIONED IT ONCE,
'BOUT HOW I KNEW DEATH GUN.
WE FOUGHT BEFORE WHEN WE
WERE STUCK IN ANOTHER GAME.
I'M SURE YOU HEARD OF IT,
"SWORD ART ONLINE."
Sinon: OH, MY GOD. I KNEW IT.
Kirito: YEAH,
I'M A SURVIVOR OF "S. A. O.,"
AND SO IS DEATH GUN,
AND BACK THEN,
HE WAS A RED PLAYER
IN THIS GUILD.
THEY CALLED THEMSELVES
LAUGHING COFFIN, P.K.ERS.
THEY HAD TO BE STOPPED,
SO ONE DAY, A PARTY WAS FORMED
TO CATCH 'EM
AND HAUL 'EM OFF TO PRISON.
I WAS IN THAT PARTY.
(SHUDDERS)
THEY FOUND OUT ABOUT OUR PLANS,
AND THEY AMBUSHED US,
AND IN THE MIDDLE OF THE CHAOS,
I KILLED TWO OF LAUGHING COFFIN.
I JUST...
CUT 'EM DOWN.
(SIGHS)
AND OVER TIME,
I MANAGED TO FORCE MYSELF
TO FORGET WHAT I DID,
TILL YESTERDAY,
WHEN I RAN INTO THE GUY
CALLING HIMSELF DEATH GUN.
Sinon: AND THERE'S NO DOUBT
HE WAS WITH LAUGHING COFFIN
THAT DAY?
YOU'RE SURE
HE WAS PART OF THAT AMBUSH?
Kirito: I AM,
ABOUT AS SURE AS I'LL EVER BE.
HE'S ONE OF THE PLAYERS
WE TOOK TO PRISON THAT DAY.
THAT'S WHY, NO MATTER WHAT,
I HAVE TO SETTLE THINGS
WITH HIM IN HERE
IN THIS WORLD.