Kirito: WHAT'S WRONG, YUI?
Yui: I HAVE A FEELING
THERE'S A LOT MORE AT STAKE HERE
THAN WE THINK.
THIS WILL REQUIRE
SOME EXPLAINING.
WHILE ALL V. R. M. M. O. s
ORIGINATE FROM THE SEED PROGRAM,
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
THEM AND "ALFHEIM ONLINE."
YOU SEE, A STRIPPED‐DOWN VERSION
OF THE CARDINAL SYSTEM
RUNS THE OTHER
ACTIVE V. R. M. M. O. s,
BUT THE ONE
THAT OPERATES THIS GAME
IS A COPY
OF THE FULL‐SPEC VERSION
THAT RAN "SWORD ART ONLINE."
Kirito: FULL‐SPEC VERSION?
Yui: THE ORIGINAL
CARDINAL SYSTEM HAD A FEATURE
WHICH COULD AUTOMATICALLY
GENERATE QUESTS.
IT WOULD LOG ON TO THE NET
AND SEARCH FOR VARIOUS LEGENDS
AND FOLKLORE
FROM AROUND THE WORLD.
THEN IT WOULD TAKE THE STORIES
IT FOUND, ADAPT THE DATA,
AND USE IT TO GENERATE
AN INFINITE NUMBER OF QUESTS.
Kirito: HOW ABOUT
THIS QUEST, THEN?
IS IT AUTOGENERATED
BY CARDINAL, TOO?
Yui: AFTER SEEING HOW THAT NPC
WAS ACTING JUST NOW,
I HAVE A FEELING IT IS.
IF THAT IS THE CASE HERE,
THEN NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO,
THIS QUEST WILL END
THE SAME WAY THE MYTH DOES.
JUST NOW, I RAN A QUICK CHECK
ON MY ARCHIVES.
ACCORDING TO MY DATA
AND TAKING INTO ACCOUNT
THE NORSE MYTHOLOGY
"A. L. O." IS BASED ON,
THIS QUEST MUST END
IN A FINAL WAR EVENT.
THE FROST GIANTS FROM JOTUNHEIM
AND NIFLHEIM
AREN'T THE ONLY ONES
WHO WANT TO ATTACK ARUN.
BELOW NIFLHEIM IS A FIERY REALM
CALLED MUSPELHEIM,
WHERE THE FLAME GIANTS LIVE.
ACCORDING TO THE MYTH,
THEY WILL ATTACK THE WORLD TREE
AND BURN IT TO THE GROUND.
Leafa: RAGNAROK,
THE TWILIGHT OF THE GODS.
UH‐UH. I DON'T BUY IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS GAME SYSTEM
WOULD DESTROY ITS OWN MAPS
ON PURPOSE.
IT'S GOTTA BE A MISTAKE.
Yui: I'M SORRY,
BUT THERE'S NO MISTAKE ABOUT IT.
THE CARDINAL SYSTEM
HAS THE AUTHORITY
TO DESTROY ITS MAPS
IF IT WANTS. I KNOW THIS,
BECAUSE THE ORIGINAL
CARDINAL SYSTEM'S LAST TASK
WAS DESTROYING AINCRAD,
THE FLOATING CASTLE
OF "SWORD ART ONLINE."
Leafa: NO WAY.
Asuna: (SIGHS)
Lisbeth: THERE GOES
MY BLACKSMITH'S SHOP.
Pina: (COOS)
Klein: THERE GO MY CHANCES
OF EVER MEETING MY SOUL MATE.
Sinon: EVEN IF
THIS RAGNAROK THING HAPPENS
AND IT ALL DELETES,
CAN'T THE SERVER BE ROLLED BACK
THE WAY IT WAS FROM ONE
OF THE BACKUPS IT'S MADE?
Yui: THE SYSTEM HAS
AN AUTOBACKUP FEATURE,
BUT THOSE FILES WON'T HELP.
IT ONLY SAVES PLAYER DATA,
NOT FIELD DATA,
SO YOU CAN'T RESTORE EVERYTHING.
All: (SIGH)
‐ Klein: OH, I GOT IT!
‐ All: HMM?
Klein: I DON'T GOT IT.
Lisbeth: YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
Klein: STOP RAZZING ME.
I WAS TRYING TO CALL A G.M.
TO SEE IF HE KNEW ABOUT THIS.
IT AIN'T HAPPENING NOW.
IT'S AFTER HOURS.
SUPPORT'S CLOSED.
Kirito: THAT FIGURES.
IT'S SUNDAY MORNING
JUST BEFORE NEW YEAR'S.
Leafa: KAZUTO,
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
Kirito: YEAH.
LET'S HURRY
AND GET TO THE LAST LEVEL.
All: RIGHT!
Minotaur: (ROARING)
Kirito: (YELLS)
Leafa: (YELLS)
Kirito: DAMN IT.
Minotaur: (ROARS)
Sinon: (GASPS) DAMN.
Leafa: THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
THE GOLD ONE'S TOUGH.
NOTHING WE DO
IS SLOWING HIM DOWN.
Kirito: YEAH.
Klein: THIS SUCKS.
IF WE ONLY HAD A MAGE
WHO CAN CAST ATTACK SPELLS
IN OUR PARTY.
Lisbeth: (GROANS)
THAT'S HILARIOUS
COMING FROM YOU.
IT WOULDN'T HELP, ANYWAY,
'CAUSE THE DUDE IN THE BACK
WITH THE HIGH RESISTANCE
TO MAGIC WOULD JUST MOVE UP.
COULD THIS GET ANY TOUGHER?
Yui: SHOCKWAVE ATTACK
COMING UP IN THREE,
TWO, ONE!
Minotaur: (ROARS)
Asuna: SOO FILLA
HAIL‐AGOOL OUSTOOL!
PLOT SUBAHL BAHNI!
KIRITO!
WE'VE ONLY GOT
ABOUT 2 1/2 MINUTES
BEFORE I'M OUT OF M. P.!
Kirito: 'KAY.
Leafa: KAZUTO, MORE THAN 2/3
OF THIS MEDALLION'S GONE DARK.
IF WE DIE NOW,
WE WON'T HAVE TIME
TO START OVER
FROM THE SAVE POINT.
Kirito: THANKS. GOOD TO KNOW.
HEY, GUYS,
THERE'S ONE THING
WE HAVEN'T TRIED YET.
IF WE USE SWORD SKILLS
WITH MAGIC,
WE MIGHT DO SOME DAMAGE
TO THIS GOLD BASTARD.
IT'LL LEAVE YOU
WIDE OPEN, THOUGH,
IT'S DO‐OR‐DIE TIME!
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY WE FOCUS
OUR ATTACK AND WIPE HIM OUT?
Klein: HELL, YEAH.
JUST SAY THE WORD,
AND HIS ASS IS GRASS.
Minotaur: (ROARING)
Kirito: SILICA,
TIME FOR YOUR BUBBLE SPELL.
Silica: RIGHT!
Kirito: READY, AND...
HIT IT!
Silica: PINA,
BUBBLE BREATH ATTACK!
Minotaur: (GROANS)
Kirito: GO!
Klein: (YELLS)
Leafa: (YELLS)
Lisbeth: (YELLS)
Silica: (YELLS)
Kirito: (YELLING)
Klein: KIRITO! (GROANS)
WE LOCKED UP!
Kirito: THIS IS IT.
(YELLING)
Klein: (GROANS) YAH!
Minotaur: (GROANS)
Kirito: (GASPS)
(CHORUS SINGING)
‐ Asuna: (YELLS)
‐ Kirito: (GASPS)
Minotaur: (GROANS)
Black minotaur: (GROWLING)
(SNORTS)
Klein: AWW.
WE KILLED YOUR PAL.
TOO BAD, FOR YOU.
(BLOWS STRIKE)
Minotaur: (BELLOWING)
(FANFARE PLAYING)
All: (CHEERING)
Sinon: (SIGHS)
Klein: OKAY, WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT MOVE YOU JUST PULLED?
Kirito: YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
Klein: OH, COME ON.
THAT WAS TOTALLY A NEW SKILL.
Kirito: WELL,
IT'S NOT REALLY A SKILL.
IT'S SKILL CONNECT.
Klein: SKILL CONNECT?
Kirito: REMEMBER
THE LAST UPDATE?
YOU KNOW IT BROUGHT A BUNCH OF
SWORD SKILLS TO "A. L. O.," RIGHT?
WELL, EVEN THOUGH WE GOT THOSE,
WE DIDN'T GET UNIQUE SKILLS
LIKE DUAL‐WIELDING
OR THE DIVINE BLADE.
Klein: HANG ON A SEC.
YOU WERE DUAL‐WIELDING JUST NOW.
Kirito: TECHNICALLY,
THAT WASN'T DUAL‐WIELDING.
Klein: HUH?
Kirito: I WAS USING
ONE‐HANDED SWORD SKILLS
WITH EACH HAND
AND ALTERNATING BETWEEN 'EM.
IF I'M LUCKY,
I CAN KEEP IT GOING
WITHOUT ANY LAG
MAYBE THREE OR FOUR TIMES.
‐ Asuna: HMM.
‐ Yui: EH?
Asuna: NO, IT'S NOTHING, YUI,
JUST DEJA VU, IS ALL.
Klein: YOU'RE NOT
OFF THE HOOK EITHER.
WHAT THE HELL'D YOU DO
JUST NOW?
Kirito: I DON'T THINK
YOU WANT TO KNOW.
Klein: OH, COME ON.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THAT BEFORE.
Kirito: IT'S AN EXTRA SKILL
I PICKED UP,
DUAL‐WIELDING.
All: (GASP)
Asuna: (SIGHS)
Kirito: DON'T POP
A BLOOD VESSEL.
ALL RIGHT. WE CAN'T
STAND AROUND CHATTING ALL DAY.
LEAFA, HOW MUCH TIME
WE GOT LEFT?
Leafa: OH, RIGHT.
AT THE PACE WE'RE GOING,
WE SHOULD HAVE
MAYBE ANOTHER HOUR OR SO.
Kirito: THAT'S IT?
YUI, DO YOU KNOW
HOW BIG THESE LAST COUPLE
OF FLOORS ARE GONNA BE?
Yui: YES. THE THIRD FLOOR
IS ABOUT 70% THE SIZE
OF THE SECOND,
AND THE FOURTH FLOOR IS
PRETTY MUCH JUST THE BOSS ROOM.
Kirito: I FIGURE
THE LAST BOSS FIGHT
WILL TAKE US
30 MINUTES TO FINISH.
THAT MEANS WE ONLY GOT ABOUT
30 MINUTES TO GET TO HIS ROOM.
Lisbeth: THAT SETTLES IT.
THE CLOCK'S TICKING,
AND THE KING OF GIANTS
IS WAITING.
LET'S GET THE LEAD OUT
AND KICK HIS GIANT ASS.
‐ Yui: DADDY!
‐ Kirito: (GROANS)
(CHUCKLES)
YOU HEARD HER.
AS SOON AS EVERYONE'S GOT
THEIR H. P. AND M. P. RESTORED,
WE'LL HIT THAT THIRD FLOOR!
All: RIGHT!
Monster: (SHRIEKS)
(METAL CLANGS)
Kirito: (PANTING)
(GASPS)
Pina: (WHISTLES)
(SQUAWKS)
Silica: HYAH!
Monster: (SHRIEKS)
Kirito: (YELLS)
Pina: (SQUAWKS)
Silica: (CHUCKLES)
Kirito: COME ON, GUYS!
THE LAST BOSS IS WAITING!
Klein: (SHRIEKS)
Woman: PLEASE, HELP ME.
LET ME OUT OF HERE.
Klein: (CHUCKLING)
(GASPS)
Kirito: IT'S A TRAP.
Lisbeth: IT'S A TRAP.
Sinon: IT'S SO A TRAP.
Klein: WELL, MAYBE IT IS.
MAYBE IT ISN'T.
Kirito: WHAT DO YOU THINK, YUI?
Yui: SHE'S AN NPC.
HER CORE PROGRAMMING
IS CONNECTED
TO THE LANGUAGE ENGINE MODULE,
JUST LIKE URD'S,
ALTHOUGH THERE IS
ONE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THEM.
THIS ONE HAS AN H. P. GAUGE.
Kirito: YEAH,
THAT'S A BIG RED FLAG.
IF SHE'S GOT AN H. P. GAUGE,
WE MIGHT HAVE TO FIGHT HER.
‐ Asuna: A TRAP.
‐ Silica: TOTALLY A TRAP.
‐ Leafa: OBVIOUSLY A TRAP.
‐ Pina: (SQUAWKS)
Kirito: IT MIGHT BE A TRAP.
IT MIGHT NOT. I DON'T KNOW.
EITHER WAY, WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO TAKE THE CHANCE.
WE CAN'T WASTE ANY MORE TIME.
WE GOTTA GET TO THRYMR ASAP.
Klein: OH, RIGHT. YEAH.
WE GOT A JOB TO DO.
Woman: DO NOT LEAVE ME, PLEASE.
I BEG YOU.
Players: EH?
Klein: I KNOW IT'S A TRAP.
I'M NOT STUPID.
BUT EVEN IF IT IS A TRAP,
EVEN IF I KNOW IT'S A TRAP,
I DON'T CARE!
I CAN'T JUST TURN MY BACK
ON SOMEONE IF THEY NEED HELP!
EVEN IF‐‐EVEN IF IT MEANS
WE FAIL THE QUEST
AND EVEN IF ARUN GETS DESTROYED,
IF I GOT A CHANCE TO DO
SOME GOOD FOR SOMEONE, I WILL,
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT BEING
A SAMURAI'S ALL ABOUT!
All: (SIGH)
Klein: DON'T WORRY, PRINCESS!
I'M COMING!
Woman: I'M FREE.
THANK YOU, FAERIE SWORDSMAN.
(GIGGLES)
Klein: NO WORRIES.
LET ME HELP YOU UP.
All: (GROANING)
Woman: NO, I CAN MANAGE IT.
(GASPS)
Klein: WHOA.
THE WAY OUT'S
KIND OF FAR, DOLLFACE.
YOU GONNA BE OKAY
TO MAKE IT ON YOUR OWN?
Woman: (SIGHS)
Klein: HMM?
Woman: I COULD,
BUT I'M AFRAID I CANNOT LEAVE
THE CASTLE JUST YET.
FOR, YOU SEE, I MUST FIRST
RETRIEVE MY PEOPLE'S TREASURE,
WHICH KING THRYMR STOLE.
IF YOU WOULD, FAERIE SWORDSMAN,
PLEASE LET ME ACCOMPANY YOU
TO THRYMR'S ROOM.
Klein: (GASPING)
Asuna: THIS IS BEYOND FISHY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
Kirito: UH‐HUH.
Klein: HEY, UH, KIRITO...
Kirito: (SIGHS)
ALL RIGHT.
I CAN'T STAND SEEING YOU BEG.
SINCE WE ONLY GOT A LITTLE
FURTHER TO GO BEFORE THE END
AND SEEING AS HOW WE DON'T KNOW
FOR SURE IT'S A TRAP...
Klein: YES!
YOU HEAR THAT?
YOU'RE COMING WITH US, GORGEOUS.
WE'LL HELP YOU BEAT
THAT JERK THRYMR.
WE'RE IN THE SAME BOAT NOW,
SO LET'S GET WET TOGETHER.
Woman: OH, THANK YOU,
FAERIE SWORDSMAN.
Klein: (GASPS)
Kirito: DELETE KLEIN'S LAST
COMMENT FROM YOUR MEMORY, YUI.
Yui: HUH?
Klein: NAME'S KLEIN.
‐ Kirito: "FREYJA."
‐ Freyja: WHAT A FINE NAME.
Kirito: HUH. SHE MUST BE A MAGE.
HER M. P.'s REALLY HIGH.
WITH THE WAY THEY GOT
THIS DUNGEON LAID OUT,
THE FINAL BOSS ROOM
SHOULD BE DOWN THOSE STAIRS.
REMEMBER, HE'S THE LAST BOSS,
SO HE'S GONNA BE WAY STRONGER
THAN THE OTHER ONES.
WHEN YOU HIT HIM,
HIT FAST, AND HIT HARD.
UNTIL WE CAN FIGURE OUT
HIS ATTACK PATTERNS,
WE'LL BE ON THE DEFENSIVE,
SO NO ONE MOVES ON HIM
TILL I SAY.
ONE LAST THING. IF YOU SEE
HIS GAUGE DROP TO YELLOW OR RED,
HIS ATTACK PATTERNS ARE GONNA
CHANGE BIG‐TIME, SO WATCH OUT.
All: MM.
Kirito: THIS IS IT, GUYS.
GET IN THERE,
AND GIVE IT ALL YOU GOT.
All: RIGHT!
Pina: (SQUAWKS)
All: (GASPING)
Asuna: SEH‐AAH, FILLA, SKEANA,
HAGGLE, HOGG, MARGLE, ILL‐TOH!
OATH, NARZA, FIYOHL, LEGGIN,
TINARDA, VALINDLE, YOTUN!
Silica: SHE BOOSTED
OUR MAXIMUM H. P.
I DIDN'T KNOW
A SPELL COULD DO THAT.
Lisbeth: (SHUDDERS)
CHA‐CHA‐CHING.
WONDER HOW MUCH YULD'S HERE?
Klein: (LAUGHS)
COOCHIE‐COOCHIE‐COO.
Thrmyr: WHO LET THE FLIES IN?
Klein: HMM?
Thrmyr: THE BUZZING
OF THEIR WINGS IS SO IRRITATING.
HMM.
(FOOTSTEPS RUMBLING)
(COINS JINGLE)
Thrmyr: I SHALL CRUSH THEM ALL
BEFORE THEY ANNOY ME
ANY FURTHER.
Kirito: (GASPING)
Thrmyr: (CHUCKLES)
WINGED ALFHEIM INSECTS.
HAVE YOU BURROWED DOWN HERE
ON THE WHIMS OF URD,
THE TROLLOP?
WRETCHES, HOW DARE
YOU ENTER HERE?
DID YOU THINK
YOU COULD STEAL MY TREASURE?
IF YOU TELL ME
WHERE I CAN FIND THAT WOMAN,
I SHALL GIVE IT ALL
TO YOU GLADLY.
Klein: HA! YOU THINK A SAMURAI
GIVES A DAMN ABOUT GOLD?
WELL, YOU CAN STICK
THAT TREASURE RIGHT UP YOUR ASS.
BETTER YET,
LET ME GIVE YOU A HAND.
Thrmyr: (CHUCKLES)
LADY FREYJA.
HOW GOOD OF YOU TO GRACE US
WITH YOUR PRESENCE TODAY.
I SEE YOU HAVE LEFT YOUR CAGE.
SHALL I TAKE IT
YOU HAVE COME TO YOUR SENSES
AND AGREED TO BECOME MY WIFE?
(LAUGHS)
Klein: SHE'S SUPPOSED
TO MARRY YOU?
Thrmyr: YES, SHE IS.
THAT IS WHY
SHE CAME TO THIS CASTLE.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, MY DEAR?
HOWEVER, THE NIGHT BEFORE
OUR WEDDING BANQUET,
I CAUGHT HER SNIFFING AROUND
MY TREASURE VAULT.
AS PUNISHMENT,
I LOCKED HER IN A CAGE OF ICE.
(LAUGHS)
‐ Leafa: HEY, KAZUTO...
‐ Kirito: HMM?
Leafa: I KNOW THIS STORY.
I READ IT BEFORE,
THRMYR AND FREYJA,
A STOLEN TREASURE,
AND SOMETHING ELSE, TOO,
BUT WHAT?
Freyja: I WILL
NOT BECOME YOUR WIFE.
THESE WARRIORS AND I ARE HERE
TO PUT AN END
TO YOUR REIGN OF EVIL.
RETURN MY TREASURE IMMEDIATELY!
Thrmyr: YES,
THAT'S THE SPIRIT, MY LOVELY.
I WOULD EXPECT NOTHING LESS
FROM THE WOMAN
WHOSE BEAUTY AND VALOR
ARE KNOWN THROUGHOUT THE LAND.
AND AS THEY SAY,
THE MORE NOBLE THE FLOWER,
THE MORE SATISFYING IT IS
TO PLUCK.
AFTER I'VE SNUFFED THE LIFE
FROM THESE INSECTS,
I SHALL SHOWER YOU
WITH EXTRA AFFECTION.
(CHUCKLING)
Klein: YOU BASTARD.
OVER MY DEAD BODY!
I, LORD KLEIN, WON'T LET YOU
LAY A FINGER ON LADY FREYJA!
Thrmyr: (CHUCKLES)
LISTEN TO THE ANGRY LITTLE FLY
BUZZING AWAY.
NOW, THEN, IT IS TIME
I BEGAN CELEBRATING
MY CONQUEST OF JOTUNHEIM.
I SHALL START
BY CRUSHING THE LIFE FROM YOU.
Kirito: HEH.
IT'S ON!
LISTEN TO YUI, GUYS!
DON'T ATTACK TILL SHE SAYS!
All: YOU GOT IT!