They looked so...
Why were they even there?
She was clearly
trying to hide them.
Do you think...
You think Yuno
could've murdered them?
Pull it together.
The thing to do
is tell the police.
She's got me.
I'm trapped.
♪ opening song ♪
I swear I didn't!
Oh... Kurusu.
Hey, what's up?
You out right now or just
not answering the door?
Sorry,
I slept late.
Hang on.
Totally my bad.
So, burning
the midnight oil, huh?
What...? No.
Somebody forget to
check in after leaving
a certain young lady's
house last night.
Oh... Yeah.
Well, let's get going.
Listen, there's, something
I really think you
ought to know about Yuno.
When I was over there.
Oh, come on!
Gentlemen aren't
supposed to kiss n' tell.
People will think I'm loose.
Please.
Two young kids?
I've been around the block.
I only care when you
don't keep me in the loop.
Fine.
Seems Uryuu was
abducted last night.
You serious?
Yup.
Gaggle of religious nut
jobs call themselves the
Omekata Cult got
their hands on her.
Least that's what
my diary tells me.
Oh okay then.
We're heading for
their shrine as we speak.
Keep your fingers crossed
things go smoothly in there.
I may need you guys
to run interference.
Thanks. Think I got it.
Look, I'm not trying to be
rude, but she wouldn't
even see the Emperor
without an appointment.
But can't you at least ask?
If she says no,
I promise to go away.
Alright fine.
If you're smart, though,
you won't get your hopes up.
You're a life saver.
Thanks.
Ai!
We got a live one.
How I am supposed to
let the cat out of the
bag about last night
without Yuno strangling it?
Think about it...
If she killed them,
what are my chances?
Stop hovering, damn it.
Hey.
Play it cool.
This should be such fun.
Guess there's a first
time for everything, huh?
She's actually okay to see
you without an appointment.
Follow me, please.
Everybody got them on?
Yeah.
But, uh...
What is this for?
Don't try to get all cute.
It's called tradition.
Yukiteru Amano.
First among the Diary Keepers;
evader of no fewer
than two Dead Ends.
And none too hard on the eyes.
His companion is a fifth wheel.
Her ladyship is through here.
Kinda creepy.
Looks like a dungeon.
It is an honor to
make your acquaintance.
I am Lady Omekata;
also known as Tsubaki Kasugano.
I do hope you will
enjoy your stay here.
I would have a closer
look at your face.
Yukiteru.
You're...
Quite.
I have been burdened
with poor vision from childhood.
Thus I spend the greater
portion of my life
holding court from this
most humble of cells.
One of the few consolations
afforded me is to write of the
many visitors I receive from
far flung corners of the globe.
Not a month ago, however,
my record of such people
began to offer details
of events yet to come.
Thus have I taken to calling
it the Clairvoyant Diary.
Upon it are written
the observations
--of those around me.
--Oh no.
This is my Diary.
I am designated Sixth among you.
No it can't be!
What am I supposed to do now?
I had the boys
downtown set up for a
raid in the event I didn't
make it out of here.
Detective, it seems
you've prepared
a raid as a
precautionary measure.
How very sharp of you.
Please, forgive my laughter.
It's just...
Your reputation precedes
you and yet you
lay prostrate before me
like a trained dog.
I assure you you have
nothing to fear from me.
I have no desire to succeed God.
The woman called Ninth
is being kept below.
You have my blessing
to do with her as you will.
No, this...
This is far too easy.
I am not one to meddle
in secular matters.
She's got a Dead End!
My thought is bent on...
...more eternal concerns.
You, though.
In the course of this
shameful game you
have already foiled
two Dead Ends.
I propose an exchange of sorts.
I shall give you Uryuu Minene.
On condition that Yukiteru
stays here and protects me.
Hell no!
We're not agreeing to that!
Dilemma.
If I don't go along with the
terms, Ninth'll inevitably
escape and more
than likely kill Sixth.
We can't have that.
What do you say?
He says no!
Please, First.
She meant it when she said
she spends most of
her time in there.
Alright.
What's the diary say
about your death...
I mean the person
coming for you?
One of the many limitations
of the scroll, I fear.
Of my enemy it says nothing.
'Kay, I made a promise to keep
watch over her for the night.
Don't wimp out.
If I may say so.
She is a threat to you.
I, cannot condescend
to trust her.
My heart tells me
that if you are not
careful you'll surely meet
your end by this girl.
Is that, like what
your diary says, or...
My intuition says.
5:50.
Yuki talks to Sixth.
Yuki looks uncomfortable after
she says something bad about me.
Don't let that woman get
inside your head, my love.
I'll kill her if she does.
Tsubaki, look out!
We've got a fire!
Someone bring water, quickly!
Hurry up!
Douse the mattresses, now!
You idiot!
You're using gasoline!
Stop!
What in the?
Was I, doing something just now?
Simpleton!
Someone bring a bucket of water!
Huh?
What am I?
What the hell's going on?!
What is wrong with
you damn people?!
Screw this!
I've got a promise to keep;
stop being a tourist and move!
--Tsubaki!
--Don't!
I forbid you!
You expect me
to just let her die?!
Yes I do!
Have you noticed
what's going on?!
We need to get
out of here right now!
Look around!
The chances of this
being anything but
a trap are so low
it's not even funny!
You're gonna die!
We're playing
right into their hands!
Look I have to do this!
Please, Yuki!
Just trust me!
Listen to yourself.
Does another person's
life mean so little to you?!
Sweetie, please.
Not now.
We'll, talk at home?
Right before you kill me
and stuff me into a closet?
What would've happened if I
hadn't run like hell last night?
Would you have added
me to your collection?
You want me to trust
you after what I've seen?
Well I'm sorry, "sweetie,"
that's just not possible!
You are certifiably
out of your mind!
Yuki.
Why are they all
trying to kill each other?
Tsubaki!
You're not hurt, are you?!
Someone disabled the sprinklers?
Kurusu fixed them, though.
I think we're gonna be okay now!
Uh, Tsubaki?
Comport yourselves
like human beings!!!
What in the?
Why am I holding this?
As for you, my friend.
I admire your bravery.
You are certifiably
out of your mind!
I know my Yuki.
He'd never say
something like that.
Sixth is behind this.
She has control of his mind.
Bitch has it coming anyway.
So, yeah...
No reason I can't
be the one to do it!
What was going on
with everyone just now?
Some sort of hypnosis,
I imagine.
Like they've been brain washed?!
This display was simply
meant to distract us.
Meaning the enemy knows
my diary's weakness.
You've got to admit, Ninth,
one less eye isn't the
end of the world.
Oh, I'm sorry would you
prefer to be called Uryuu?
It's a good look for you.
I believe the treatment worked.
Treatment?
You gouged out my eye
on the off chance
I'd spill the beans
about First.
Plotting your escape?
I wouldn't waste my
time if I were you.
Between you and her
ladyship, there's no contest.
Screw you!
Oh It's nothing personal.
You see, in Rock/Paper/Scissors,
paper beats rock,
rock beats scissors and
scissors beat paper.
That's just how it is;
all three elements
are locked into that
dynamic permanently.
Just as your fabled
ability to escape
will always lose out
to her clairvoyance.
Interesting.
All is quiet up above.
I wonder what could have
quelled their little fracas?
What's he talking about?
It's been quiet as
the grave down here.
Come on, man.
Pick up.
What's Kurusu up to?
The person responsible
for this outrage
is clearly on the premises.
The question is where?
Behold the Diary of
Clairvoyance, Yuki.
As it unfurls, so
do the thoughts
of my thousand-odd adherents.
There!
An outsider's combing
through the lodge.
They must be
confronted immediately.
Acolytes!
That diary's the business.
No wonder she caught Ninth.
Sure glad she's on our side.
Wait a sec.
Look at this!
What do you see?
Someone suspicious
near the back gate.
But the lodge stands on the
other side of the complex.
Two for the price of one.
Crap!
There's another guy!
A suspicious figure charges
through the front gate.
There are three?
What the hell just happened?
It's as if the shrine
is being infested!
Hypnosis.
They're turning your
followers against you!
The picture this
creates is too chaotic!
In tandem, these
futures are a mess!
Of course.
It's important to bear in
mind that no element of
the game is without
its own drawback.
For example the diary of
Sixth is susceptible
to holes created by
information overload.
Who is this creep?
Holy!
Yuno...
Look, just give us
a minute, okay?
Maybe you could
wait outside for me?
'Kay. If that's what you want.
Don't keep me waiting
too long though.
Seriously, Yuno with
an axe is not a good sign.
Surely you're "hip" enough to
have seen one of these before.
It may look like a prop...
But in actuality,
it is an engine of
self-transformation!
Transform, to!
He's insane.
I'm looking at a crazy person.
You sure you're alright?
Always the perfect
gentleman, isn't he?
C'mon.
It's not fair for you to
hog him from the rest of us.
Yuki's help is essential.
But I'll only need him
for a little while longer.
That's too damn bad!
Besides, he won't be much
use to you after you're dead!
Oh crap!
The bad guys are making a move!
The flag?
Oh no... Another Dead End's
been triggered
for you, love.
Transformation tights!
Transformation gloves!
Transformation mask!
You're a freak.
Madam, madam, madam...
You mean a freak who rocks!
You're the Twelfth.
Chaos rules the day up there!
Give me a break.
You can hear them?
From down here?
If Sixth can espy all
that transpires,
I can hear all that transpires!
It's because
you're blind, right?
Reckoning!
I will be their reckoning!
Die evil cultists!
Wait, evil?
C'mon.
What's the Omekata cult ever
done besides being zealots?
Do you question
the judgment of Justice?
Evil wears many guises and I
know each and every one of them!
The wretches above us
are no match for me!
Vice cannot triumph
over righteousness!
I wipe the slate clean,
so that goodness may thrive!
No villainy can foil my
plan to obliterate them!
Oh yeah?
That a fact?
Your ointment's attracted a fly.
Someone I don't think
you were planning on.
What am I gonna do?
Sixth and I are both
as good as dead.
If I could just find where
the enemy's operating from.
Cut it out!
What the hell are you doing?!
Grab an axe.
We've gotta kill the corpses.
She's on to me!
These aren't the
kind that stay down.
They've totally been hypnotized
into playing possum?!
No!
My Rock/Paper/Scissors
metaphor still holds!
I'll just use Sixth.
She'll be my decoy
for saving my man!
Something wrong?
Vice can't triumph
over righteousness.
I...
I don't understand.
Aw, poor dope.
You've never met Yuno Gasai.
Time to choose, Yuki.
Choose what?
Stick with me and
get out of this alive.
Or stay with the whore
and say goodnight.
What is she?
Better hurry.
♪ closing song ♪
Compiling the accounts of
each and every visitor into
something like a coherent
whole is exceedingly difficult.
This apparition
is strange to me.
Who or what is it, exactly?
Does it condescend to treat my
chamber like a sidewalk cafe?
Why does it drag a
futon across the floor?
The creature intends
to sleep here?!
What manner of specter invades
one's dwelling so nonchalantly?!
Poor lil' thing.
I could sit here all night
and she'd never notice.
My eyesight isn't that bad!
By what right do you challenge
my home's sanctity?!
So basically you've been
cherry-picked by the powers
that be to take part in a
one of a kind competition.
You might have told me before
making yourself at home.