What the...?
So Deus is sending
us text messages now?
"The ability to add diary
keepers." That can happen?
More keepers?
You got to be kidding me.
♪ opening song ♪
So, what kind of
knowledge did the Lord High
Referee drop on you guys?
Uh...
Give me a sec.
Hey, Kousaka mind if
I borrow your cell phone?
Nuh-uh!
Just be careful, yeah?
That bad boy's a full-fledged
Future Diary now!
But, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Break that phone
and my ass is dead.
What the balls
are you doing, man?!
Yup!
I'm checking out!
Well, guess I was right.
And for Kousaka's sake,
I'm glad you were!
In that case...
Eighth's diary has to
offer server functionality.
Grow a pair already, would ya?
How is he still
alive after that?
At first blush, it would seem
that Eighth is "spawning"
new keepers but the truth
is far more pedestrian.
The server is the
one true Future Diary.
All the others are mere
knockoffs, subordinate to it.
That would be the reason you
didn't coil into
oblivion just now.
That so wasn't cool, man!
How am I supposed to bask
in my future
rockitude now, huh?!
We couldn't risk the
enemy using that information
to keep tabs on us.
Dude, let a brother
back up his crap first!
Sorry about that.
The plot thickens?
Three days from now
they invade my house!
Tracking us from afar
doesn't longer an option.
They're going to be
anxious to make a move.
What should I do?
I can't rely on Yuno.
You didn't just do
that... Darling why?
Screw you.
I know it was the
right decision but still,
how am I supposed
to fend for myself?!
The question is, how do we keep
our sundry enemies at bay?
Nishijima assigning some
guards would be a fair start.
We need to stash Yuki where
they're not gonna look.
A little bird told me that
Kousaka's house would
be the perfect spot to hide him.
Wha?
Alright then
everything's settled.
What do mean it's settled?!
Does that plan get
your seal of approval?
You mean, you guys are
really gonna help me out?
All due respect,
man, but tough titty...
You seem a bit shocked and awed.
What, you didn't think we were
gonna do you a solid Yuki?
No phone.
Just tell us what's in your gut.
"We'll show you ours
if you show us yours,"
which is a crude idiom,
but apropos.
So do you want us to help you,
or mind our own business?
Uh...
I...
I can't do this on my own.
Good, because we
weren't about to let you.
I called up our benefactor.
You'll have
round-the-clock protection
for the next three days.
If anything happens,
radio for help.
Yeah.
I got it.
We'll come up with a
plan to fight off those
three subordinate diary users
once we're at Kousaka's.
Yuno's still an issue, though.
Her diary feeds her a constant
drip of information as to
your whereabouts.
But we have no such
window into her doings.
Long as she holds the tactical
high-ground we have to brace
for the possibility
that she could
blindside us at
any given moment.
Blindside us how?
Yuki, she might regard
your recent escape
as an irreparable betrayal.
She might want me dead?!
Who is it?
Just in time.
Grab a plate!
Heya, Mom.
The last time Mom and
I had dinner together
we owed the meal
to psycho-stalker.
So... um...
Go ahead.
Well...
Aren't you going to ask why
the police wanted Yuno and me?
I mean...
Awesome segue, Einstein.
Tell ya what.
You've been through
a rough patch lately,
and I'm only going to make it
worse by picking away at it.
If you want to unburden your
soul, then knock yourself out.
Otherwise, I'll wait 'til
you're ready to clue me in.
Thanks for being cool.
That said...
Huh?
Don't leave me
in the dark forever.
We got a deal?
Yeah.
Uh, question.
Isn't that, like,
a lot of potato salad?
Totally.
The three of us would've
exploded if we ate all that.
Three of us?
Yuno couldn't stick
around tonight.
She was here?!
Duh.
Who do you think
made this dinner?
She said you'd
need to be well-fed
for what she has
in store for you.
Got to make sure you
rise to the occasion, huh?
Let's go over
the plan, shall we?
First, we deposit the
redoubtable Yuki
at Kousaka's house
for safekeeping.
Nishijima sends over cops.
We'll be guarded
round-the-clock.
What good are the
police going to be
against people who
know the future?
Let's just say.
I've taken all that
well into account.
Yo...
Home, twelve o'clock.
Good.
--What?!
Not too shabby.
Can I just drive
through the gate?
Sure.
So all this is
Kousaka's front yard?!
You're filthy
frigging rich, dude!
Gramps was rich.
I'm filthy frigging lucky.
My plan requires ample
space if it's going to work.
After we've lured the enemy to
this modest homestead they will
soon find themselves
hoist by their own petard.
Observe.
How's a cell phone
tower gonna help us?
What if it were to malfunction
when they attack?
Oh yeah!
If the tower doesn't work,
they can't get updates
from Eighth's server!
Exactly.
They won't be privy
to the future anymore.
Granted, this will only work
against those with
subordinate diaries.
This is a little something
I threw together
so we can disable
the tower from up here.
Heads up, guys.
Eighth's underlings
are gonna make
a play for us in three minutes.
Squad A to HQ.
We've got eyes on the targets...
they're on the property.
They're here!
Hands at the ready, Yuki.
But don't flip those switches
'til I give you the word.
Well?
See them?!
Not yet.
But the fight is still young.
We need to make sure
they're well away from the
entrance so they
don't simply retreat.
The hell?!
Power's out!
They're inside flip the switch!
I don't want to be a buzz-kill,
but I'm still rocking
three bars over here!
Of course!
No power's running to the box!
It's like they knew in advance!
Noo... no way.
We were the only ones
who knew what was up.
Just the five of us!
No one else!
Unless.
Are you trying
to get us killed?!
Hey!
Found ya!
Aw!
You've had me worried to death!
But, have no fear, honey-bun!
I'm gonna save you!
Oh, I've missed you, baby!
What the hell is she doing here?
Is she gonna drag me off again?!
Yuki, Look at me!
Yuki, I'm here for you!
Hey. Maybe you should
come up here, Yuno.
Yuki told me he'd prefer that.
Are you nuts?!
Kousaka and I will
head over to the
cell phone tower and
disable it manually.
I know it's asking a lot,
but you need to keep
that girl placated.
We can't have her running amok.
Why me?
Step lively now.
We haven't a moment to waste.
You first.
Says here it'll take them thirty
minutes to knock out the tower.
We just have to run
down the clock 'til they do.
Yuki, darling.
Why'd you bind my hands?
'Cause without them tied,
you scare the crap outta me.
Wouldn't I be more useful
with my hands untied?
Nishijima!
Son of a bitch!
Ah, check it out, Marco!
There's Yuki.
That drab little pork-chop
second from the left.
C'mon, Ai.
He's no more than
tofu on a good day.
Don't be a jerk... He's
lasted this long, hasn't he?
Oh crap!
How'd they get here so fast?!
Give it up.
You may have got
the drop on me once.
But I'm about to open up a can
of police brutality on your ass!
Yeah about that!
Night-night, little piggy!
Checking that highlight reel,
it's clear you zigged when
you should have zagged!
You and your boner
for counterattacks.
Not that it's gonna save
your ass either way
but I'm gonna give you
a sneak-peek, pretty boy!
Check it out!
The Undefeated Champion Diary!
It tells me when to bust
out a counter attack
and plant whatever
chump's in my way!
You wanna come down here
and give it a closer look?
Goodness.
So Marco and Ai have made
it into the mansion already?
Very well!
In that case, just keep
an eye on them for me.
Would you, Ta?
Yeah...
Sure thing.
Everybody!
Run for it!
Shouldn't we be
chasing after them?
No point in breaking
a sweat, Mar.
He's not getting away.
Hello, boys.
Don't forget.
I've got the details on any guy
I'm gonna flirt with,
including where.
First is a little young but a
gal could do a lot worse.
What'd I tell ya?
How'd they find us?!
I'll buy you guys some time!
Props for the moxie,
honey but I don't like girls!
Sorry!
Mao, no!
Are you okay?!
We have to keep climbing, Yuki!
What are you doing?!
The others are still down there!
I don't care about them.
My darling Yuki is safe.
That's all that matters to me.
Now, be a good boy
and untie me, kay?
Come on.
Look at me, Yuki.
I can't.
Why not?
You know what those
two down there are
going to do if they catch you.
But I can kill them in a jiffy!
Then what?
You take me prisoner again?
The last time I trusted you, you
drugged me and took me hostage.
Sorry if I'm not tripping over
myself to get your hands untied.
No, I...
I had to keep you safe!
I can't protect you with
my hands like this, Yuki!
Okay.
End of the line, kid.
This is it.
I'm gonna die here.
Yuki, can you read me?
Come in, Yuki!
Akise, help!
It sounds like you're busy.
I'll just pull the lever
and hope for the best.
Son of a--!
The reception's for
balls up in here!
Awesome!
The cell-phone tower's
out of commission.
Meanwhile, I've got a working
diary and a big knife.
I'll just chase them
off or something!
Wouldn't you know it.
They jammed our phones.
Typical.
All that running around
was bad for my do, anyway.
Yeah.
It did a number on
my makeup, too.
Might as well ditch them.
They ain't gonna help us.
Adios, useless diary.
That's a good thing.
We qualify for an upgrade.
Wait a sec... are those?!
Pardon my French, kiddies,
but you all are fucked!
"I don't understand it,
Marco how did you know
we were gonna destroy
your diaries?!" Simple!
'Cause we're smarter than you!
You played right into our hands
and now you're
gonna pay the price!
Oh yeah!
Guess I'll give you the formal
introduction before I kill you.
I am Seventh!
Marco Ikusaba!
I'm Seventh, also.
Ai Mikami.
[BOTH] Our Exchange Diaries
are the real deal!
--Game over, chumps!
They're actual keepers!
Yuki, please!
I am begging you to untie me!
I'll never take you
prisoner again I swear it!
I swear on my life!
I adore you with all of
my heart, Yukiteru Amano!
Just this once believe in me!
I can't set her free!
She belongs in a
damn straightjacket!
But, if I don't set her free
then we're talking
two against one.
And that one's
quick with a knife!
God, are the girls
even alive down there?!
I got to live.
Whatever it takes!
I got to win!
Give me the knife.
I love you, too.
Well?
Fair enough.
We don't have a problem
taking you out first, girlie.
Tell me something kiddo.
Do you believe in the
all-redeeming power of love?
My Future Diary is
a testament to our love.
It keeps tabs on my baby,
so I can protect her 24-7.
Meanwhile, my Future Diary
keeps tabs on him.
I've got Marco's fine-ass
backside, and he's got mine.
By the power of
our phones combined.
Behold the bad-assery
of true frigging love!
Uh, congrats?
Do I have to
spell it out for you?
This is gonna be a rumble
between couples, a love match!
And our love has steamrolled way
worse than the two of you!
This ain't gonna take long if
you guys just stand there!
Don't throw knives
at my beloved.
Whoa.
That was amazing!
How about two at once?!
Yuki said I was amazing!
What the hell?!
Impossible!
One compliment from
Yuki and I feel like I could
deflect these knives all day
long without even trying!
You're doing such a great job!
Just keep it up!
Hey lover.
Don't panic,
but I'm fresh outta shivs.
What?
Already?!
I'm doing great!
Yuki said so!
--Uh-oh.
Hold onto your asses!
--Bye!
Huh?!
Hinata and Mao are gone!
Why'd you drag us out here?
I can drag you
back in if ya want...
but it's gonna get hot in there.
I don't think that's
what you want.
Here it comes.
Just in case we
didn't seal the deal
our pal Ta had orders
to torch the place.
Ai...
Let's book.
That's it?
You're just running away?
Who said anything about running?
We still got to
school those poseurs!
The girls are in danger!
I have to rescue
them from Seventh!
But...
Is it okay to use Yuno?
I mean, can I trust her?
You can use me all you want.
Bet you you're wondering
if that's safe, but it is.
I'll even tell you
how to sell me on it.
"Help me save those
other girls, Yuno.
And I'll pretend to be your
boyfriend, just like before."
Okay, then.
I can do pretend.
Hell, it's not like
I have a choice.
I accept.
Time for round two!
Did you think we
were giving up that easy?
Yuno!
Ai!
Once I turn you and your
boyfriend inside out,
Yuki will love me!
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
What just happened?
Yuno!
Yuno.
Please!
Wake up!
Why didn't you help
your woman, you little punk?
When a girl is in trouble.
you jump through
fire and if there's
a knife or a bullet you take it!
Why are you so spineless?!
Huh?!
No, it's not my fault.
She told me.
I could use her.
You're a waste of oxygen.
You know that don't you?
No, it isn't my fault!
I know it was cowardly to
hang back the way I did!
I know it was!
But I...
I can't!
I'm just too weak!
Go to hell.
Our plan was all for naught.
Yuki and Yuno's
diaries were taken
as spoils of battle by Seventh.
Yuno's been unconscious
ever since the ordeal.
And Hinata and Mao
were both badly injured.
This round proved to be
a resounding failure.
At least the firefighters made
good time getting there.
A minute more and we'd have lost
you both to smoke-inhalation.
Sir.
I came to take a quick
look at your head injury.
Speaking of, how'd
you receive it, anyway?
Man?
Woman?
Both?
What kind of diary did they use?
Huh?
Diary?
Aw, come on now.
Don't make me beg, kid.
I want to know
everything about them.
Why are you here?
♪ closing song ♪
My boss Deus has
decided you're gonna
be one of his twelve
diary keepers.
Cool, huh?
Well isn't he sweet?
I'll go make us some tea.
How does Miss Bobble head get
around with a noggin like that?
I'm gonna trip her to see
if she can get up again.
You know...
For science.
What was that for?
My bad.
Sorry.
You look troubled, Murmur.
What ails you?
Fine, she flipped.
But I can't figure
out how the tea cups
knew to flip along with her!
Huh?