Why bother fighting
it, you know?
This is where I belong.
Rise and shine!
Got everything you need?
Did Dad fall in or what?
Step off.
I'm an old man.
Gotta shake the dew off
the lily 'fore we leave.
Ugh.
Come on you're taking forever.
You got lunch packed up
and ready to go, yeah?
What?
Oh!
Crap, I left it sitting
on the counter.
Hold on a second guys!
Between you and me,
Yuk'-- for a gal so well put
together your mom's
a whole lot of mess.
That's a hearty laugh.
Feeling good?
Why wouldn't I be?
I've been dreaming of this day.
Really.
♪ opening song ♪
All in a day's work.
Ninth is toast and Yuki's
become a Lost Boy.
Now to tie the bow.
Can't let you being dead quash
the whole Cause
and Effect thing.
Let's just patch up
that little ouchie, huh?
You're welcome.
Right... Let's kick off the
Third Iteration, boys and girls!
Get cracking, Second.
Kill the 3.0 you before
she causes problems.
Shouldn't be hard.
Not like I haven't
done this already.
It's how the game
is played, right?
No eggs, no omelet.
Yuki's third incarnation
is waiting for me.
I have no regrets.
I'll just pay my
respects to this Yuki
and move on to the next one.
No regrets at all.
Da... Dad.
Mom.
I...
Wow.
Kind of sucks to
see yourself like this.
Naive; no one's death
on your conscience.
Who are you?
Nobody.
Someone I'm pretty sure you know
better than you think you do.
Try this on for size;
how about I lay out
for you what the
future has in store?
I don't understand.
How would you?
Hey. Kind of my thing...
I've got a finger on the
pulse of Big Daddy Time.
Have a listen to what
you're going to miss out on.
Your bipolar witch
of a mom is gonna
plummet deeper and
deeper into depression.
Dad's gonna start working
late to avoid a scene.
You might catch a glimpse
of him if you're lucky.
Mom'll get paranoid
and start taking her
frustrations out on you.
The abuse will get so bad
sometimes you just wanna die.
The good news is,
when you finally crack you'll
turn the tables and give them
a taste of their own medicine.
You just wanted
them to understand
what they were
putting you through.
You never intended it
to go as far as it did,
but everything went haywire.
Tough luck, huh?
Not your problem
anymore, though.
I'm giving you
an honest-to-god out.
No.
What?
This isn't fair.
Things haven't
gotten that bad yet.
Does it matter?! I give
you my guarantee;
in a month's time you
will be miserable!
So?
Right now mom needs me.
And sure dad
works all hours, but...
I don't love him any less for
what he must be going through.
Maybe the future is bad.
But there's a future
beyond that, isn't there?
I'll get through it.
I'd forgotten.
This was when I still
thought there was hope for us.
What...
What happened to me?
Screw this!
It's not about your future
anymore, it's about mine!
I get it.
It's someone you love.
I can tell.
Son of a!
Why has Causality stopped
behaving all of a sudden?
Where's the mix up?
Oh hell.
Yo.
Slow poke.
Something wrong?
I'm sorry.
I, I can't.
I just can't.
You're joking, right?
Sweetheart, c'mon.
You've been all about
this trip for months now.
This isn't right.
What isn't?
I can't explain it to you I just
feel like there's something.
I dunno...
Something, more important
this is keeping me from.
I shouldn't go.
The hell's going on here?
Oh my god.
Shit. Heads up,
we got a roofer!
Oh no.
--Sweetheart, don't!
--Get me a negotiator.
Wait! Stop!
The site's not safe yet!
Round up a couple
officers and comb the
area for anyone who looks
like they need a medic!
On it, sir!
Ugh! This version of Reality is
coming apart at
the frigging seams!
Second!
Kill the girl so you can
take her place already!
We're on a collision course!
I've never seen the
future scramble
to rewrite itself like this.
If this keeps up we're dead.
Try to hang in there
for me, alright?
We've got help on the way.
Hold on a second.
Don't I know you?
Lady Tsubaki.
This was discovered
in your parents' car.
What is it?
It appears to be
some kind of bomb.
Impossible.
Who would take such
issue with my parents
that they'd resort to homicide?
Damn it, get your hands off me!
Funatsu?
I curse the day you
were brought into this world!
You would have the
Founders' blood on your
hands just to wrest
control of their followers?
You old fool.
Mark me, child!
Pushed out from their shadow
you'd wither like an
orchid in the light of day!
Mark me!
This institution will not
bow to evil intrigues!
Our mission is to help the meek,
not rule them like a
medieval monarch!
Oh great.
Tsubaki's future just
got a makeover!
No, no, no!
She's supposed to
be a cynical despot
who leads her flock off a cliff!
Fifth's mom and
dad were supposed
to be charter
members of the herd!
Now the little rugrat's
gonna grow up
without a chip on his shoulder!
Exploiting the chaos
for quick financial gain?
Or perhaps you intended
a bit of foul play?
No matter!
Justice prevails!
Of all the freaks in this
cesspool of a town,
I have to run into
a festooned vigilante!
Silence, trash!
You shall call me
"The Defender."
Ah.
I was curious why the dogs
weren't raising Cain with all
this ungodly racket going
on in the streets.
Looks like you busted me, pop.
My dear.
However did you manage to
bring these creatures to heel?
Well. I'm pretty sure they
can tell I'm your daughter.
I've been using my
morning jog as an
excuse to drop in
and check on them.
Impressive.
I hadn't the faintest idea.
Hey, maybe you could, I dunno,
teach me some techniques?
What business could the mayor
possibly have with an orphanage?
Ah.
Oh.
Wait!
Beg pardon?
Help us secure funding?!
Hello?
Oh, hey Ai.
What's up?.
Huh?.
Yeah, we can hear them,
but nothing major's near us.
Cool.
Just checking in.
They're okay, right?
Whatever's going on
hasn't bothered them.
The sirens are nearby,
but they can't tell
what the fuss is about.
They'll have something about it
on the news tomorrow morning.
Get some sleep.
You're certain,
Mr. Mayor?
Ironically enough, if I
intend to change the
future I've no
choice in the matter.
Our clever little
prototype has prophesied
my untimely demise, you see.
Mustn't have that.
The game's design
was ill-advised.
I am fated to fall
quite dramatically
unless we abandon it outright.
Point one, according
to First's diary, I lose.
Point two: the winner
shall leave this universe
to its ruin in favor of
an alternate past.
Clearly we needs must
reconsider the contest.
My successor shall be
chosen by other means.
The domino effect; every
user's fate is changing.
If this keeps up,
the game itself won't even
be a thing anymore!
Then what the hell
am I gonna do?!
I love him.
Everything I've done?
It's been for him.
All of it.
Up to and including killing you.
Yuno.
Dad.
I didn't mean...
I'm sorry.
I know this can't be making a
whole lot of sense to you.
Just come on, son.
I wish I could.
But, if I do, something
in me's gonna give.
And not for the better.
This is about
the girl, isn't it?
The one you were dreaming about.
Remember?
You told us that she
was always there for you.
Yuno?
Oh no!
Mom, you're here.
Darling!
Saika.
Oh god!
Hi...
Mom.
Sweet pea.
Go to her.
We're old news, champ.
You've got a life to live.
We're not in the business
of holding you back;
we want you to
be happy.
How much of my
life did I throw away,
dreaming of the moment
when mom and dad
would finally come around?
Is this karma's idea of
a consolation prize?
Freeze!
Are you the one responsible for
what happened to this place?!
He did it.
I'll change this
world's future to save her.
My darling Yuki rewrote history,
brought this Yuno and
her parents back together.
He did it.
You're about to remember.
Good luck.
I think her name's just about
on the tip of your tongue.
Am I right?
It'll come to you soon.
Bear in mind:
it belongs to someone
closer to your heart
than even this dream.
Mom.
Dad.
No worries.
You got this.
After this the next word
you utter will bring
you to yourself.
Yuno.
What have I done?
What the hell have I done.
Yuno!
No...
No.
It's all wrong.
You weren't
supposed to have this!
Yuno!
It's someone you love.
I can tell.
I get it.
It is...
A man I would forsake
reality just to be with.
Yuno!
That's what love is.
Doing what you have to.
Yuno!
Making the ultimate sacrifice!
Death is nothing!
Yuno!
Was that a gunshot?
Why.
Yuno...
Tell me...
Let me save you.
For once.
Aw damn it.
My second incarnation.
Been a while, hasn't it "1.0?"
We haven't really talked since
you sealed me up in this thing.
Kudos to that, by the way;
I can honestly tell you
I never saw it coming.
Payback's gonna be
a real bitch, though.
Owie!!!
Idiot.
Why would you chose me over
a world where everything you'd
ever wanted was right
there at your fingertips?
Yuno...
I want you to stab me.
My baby girl.
Mom.
You get why, don't you?
You don't belong here.
I know.
Good.
When I die, you'll have a
place that you can call home.
I understand.
If this is what you
really want me to do.
Eureka!
If she kills First we can
salvage this train wreck!
I can think of worse ways to go.
At least I can say it was you.
You're a freak.
You know that?
What have you done?
This is the place
I wanna call home.
Damn you.
We had a deal, remember?
I'm not gonna be
the one to kill you.
Yuno!
No rewrites this time.
Let the future be what it is.
This isn't what I fought for!
Yuki.
I want you kissing me
to be the last thing I know.
Okay.
How about that.
I belong here after all.
Now a kiss like
that is worth dying for.
I, love...
Yuno.
And the winner is First!
All hail Yukiteru Amano!
Buck up, son!
No time for tears.
We gotta go!
Wait!
No!
Yuno.
Yuno!
According to authorities,
international terrorist
Uryuu Minine is still at
large somewhere in Japan.
Sakurami police remain on
high alert for the
foreseeable future.
Wow.
Sucks to have your job.
Third me's a real
pain in the ass.
I'm glad you find it so funny.
Chill, Dragnet.
Play your cards right and you're
bound to catch me eventually.
Baby, you have no idea.
Detective Nishijima.
Where the hell are you?
Thought you were
supposed to be my ride.
Oh crap!
Sorry!
On the way, sir!
Well don't just
sit there like that.
You've got to have
something on your mind.
You really need to get
yourself a better hobby.
And as if I needed another
reason to hate the bastard,
he said the hair made
me look like a tool!
Then you remembered
he's the one who signs
your paychecks and you
decided to be the better man.
Well yeah!
It's what I do.
Lookie there.
Yay!
Have fun doing whatever
it is you guys do.
Shall we, madam?
I'm ready when
you are, Mr. Mayor.
What's on the docket for today?
I'm afraid that's classified.
Kind of hard to tell who's
trying to hypnotize who.
Is that what they're doing?
I'm not gonna tell
you what I thought.
Ahoy, mates!
All ashore who's going ashore!
--Coming!
Does the Observer
have anything to relay,
or have the boundaries
remained intact?
Everything's cool, chief.
So far no one's tried
to run interference
from any neighboring dimensions.
An auspicious state.
So?
How'd the whole road trip
thing with your parents go?
Oh cool; is that like a diary?
Yep.
It's a scrapbook
for family stuff.
Here we are at the planetarium.
Wow. That's sounds
super awesome.
I haven't been to one
of those things in forever.
Give it here; I wanna see!
It's a little weird keeping a
diary on your phone, though.
Wanna know what's really weird?
I think it will help me remember
something I've forgotten.
What are you talking about?
Like what?
Don't really know.
You are so random.
Yeah.
It's just...
Whatever.
You okay?
How long has it been
since I became god?
A thousand years?
Ten thousand?
I'm so bored.
I've read this stupid
manga a bazillion times.
I could draw it in my sleep.
C'mon, boss give me something
to do; I'm dying over here.
Quit sulking and use your badass
powers to make something
of this void already.
What would be the point?
A void is all that
makes sense without her.
Yeah...
So you been saying
for millennia,
Sure all the iterations of
this universe are sealed off.
But why not just do
what anyone else would
in this situation and
find a new girl?
If you'd ever had
your heart broken
you'd know that's a
stupid question.
Still. You gotta be the only
other person in existence?
Damn good thing
I've grown fond of you.
I've heard it all
before, Murmur.
Let it go.
I always wonder what became
of Yuno's third incarnation.
Is she living the life
she wanted?
God, I wish I could
stop thinking it mattered.
It's beyond over;
it's ancient history.
This diary's the
only other thing
I allow to exist in this
version of Reality.
♪ closing song ♪
Yuki?
That was 10,000 years,
and I felt every one of them!
Yuki's finally
making a new world,
but unless he gets antsy
and pops in a cheat-code,
I'm still gonna have
oodles of time to kill.
Wow!
Our new home base
is looking pretty nifty!
And neither of them
have any idea
that I snuck my way in here!
Guess I'd better get to work
prepping a brand
new version of the game!
Huh?
Thought I heard
something just now.
Jackpot!
Well, no point messing
with the classics:
The Radar, The Searcher,
The Organizer, and The Supplier.
Now I'll just punch it up
with some new elements.
Enter The Jammer!
Yeah, and The Copy!
Don't forget The Select!
How about The Fake?!
The Response would be cool!
Give them the Random!
Huh?!
Too many Murmurs!