Um. Okay.
Ha-ha.
Very funny.
C'mon.
You're scaring me!
Mom.
Dad.
Help me, please.
Yuki.
♪ opening song ♪
And I'd like everyone to bear in
mind the current unpleasantness
as they make their way home.
Monitor.
Dismissed.
Court's open, right?
Ours for the claiming, dude.
Shame we don't
have enough people.
So we find somebody.
It's not like it's hard.
Hey, Amano.
You game?
Bad idea.
Dude. Really?
He's not going to
be into it, trust me.
Creep's a wallflower.
Is that why his face
is buried in that
frigging cell phone
twenty-four seven?
What's all that crap about?
Who knows.
I heard he keeps like
a diary or something.
Miss Gasai I'd appreciate
it if you could deliver
these to the faculty
lounge on your way out.
Happy to sir.
I'll get right on it.
I could also use your
help in the library,
if you can spare the time.
Sure.
I'm what you might call a
bystander, a casual observer.
Always have been, really.
I started begging off of sports
and stuff in grade school.
So, now people pretty
much leave me alone.
Guess I keep a journal out
of boredom, to be honest.
I mean, what else
was I going to do?
Don't get me wrong,
I have friends.
They just happen to be,
well, kind of imaginary.
Deus.
Yukiteru.
A moment please.
I am amending a
finer point of causality.
Sounds like somebody's
got a lot on their plate.
Reality benefits
from the occasional jolt.
You're not going to,
like, I don't know,
spark a war or
anything are you?
You dislike violence?
Wheels within wheels, lad.
Just you wait and see.
Deus Ex Machina,
lord of space and time.
That thing we call "The
Universe?" That's his baby.
Again with the diary?
How does a kid like you have
that much to write about?
Uh. Well.
I mean, it's not like I'm
writing a memoir or anything.
I just like to jot down the when
and where of things, you know?
Things like the fact that
you're lousing up my bed.
So jot this down.
Wow, Murmur, way to be mature.
Way to not have your
entries be all random.
That's the whole point.
If I tried to organize them,
there'd be too much of me
in this thing for it
to be objective.
Kay.
Besides, it's not as if I'd have
much to say otherwise.
My phone is my whole world.
That and this place.
Are you lonely?
Not really.
Given the opportunity
to reinvent yourself,
however, what would you do?
Suppose I bestow upon you the
ability to foresee the future?
Who's texting me?
Consider it my gift to you.
From my own phone?
Out with it.
What are you cooking up now?
A diversion of sorts.
Whatever you say, old man.
I can always pinch myself.
Oh, give me a break!
Somebody, get down here
and open this door right now!
Oh god, not like this.
Please I'm not ready.
What's this all about?
"April twenty-second, 6:59 a.m.
Scored a double bull's-eye
doing my morning routine."
"7:05 a.m., home.
The news ran a thing
about the serial killer again.
Another woman was murdered.
They think the guy
took a shortcut
through our school
to shake the cops."
Wait...
Did I sleep-text?
And how are all
these from today?
Whatever.
Whoa, dude!
Nice!
In other news...
The body of a young woman,
thought to be the latest
victim in a string of
serial killings that began
several months ago,
was found brutally
stabbed not far from
a school in the
Sakurami district.
The special task
force appointed to
bring the killer to
justice maintains
that this latest
murder fits the
perpetrator's so-called
escalating profile.
Another one, huh?
The killer is thought to have
fled capture in this instance by
using the nearby
school as a shortcut,
suggesting a familiarity
with the building...
How could I?
No.
Just a freaky
coincidence, that's all.
Has to be.
This is unusual.
I ran into Kousaka and
Shiraishi on my way to school.
Slow down, man!
Hey!
My bad, I figured you
were way ahead of me.
Okay, that's freaky.
I never see these guys here!
They're on the track team.
They should be at practice!
This is really starting
to weird me out.
April twenty-second, 9:30 am.
School, class 2-B.
Pop quiz in math.
This can't be a coincidence.
Wait a second.
I've got the answers?
Are they correct?
Yo, dude.
You like ace the test or what?
Well, I don't know about that.
It's not like I can
compete with you right?
Why you got to be
such a little suck-up?
12:32 p.m.
Classroom.
Kousaka gives me a
hard time at lunch again.
2:05 p.m.
Home Ec class.
Satonaka cuts her hand
and has to go to the nurse.
Okay, this is insane.
"4:12pm, walking home.
Ran into a couple of detectives
doing a sweep around the school.
They're on the
serial killer case."
Can my phone see?
Quite so.
I have an inkling you'll find
prognostication very handy.
This is impossible!
You're a figment of
my imagination,
how does that translate into
knowing what my future is?
I mean, you...
I thought you up and I don't
know what's coming next!
Do you believe imagination
and reality to be
mutually exclusive habitats
for an entity of my stature?
He's a god.
He lives where he wants.
And beware the boon of a god.
Yours in particular
comes at a price.
A diary of this kind
and its user are as one.
Should your phone come
to ruin, so shall the
march of days it serves as
a privileged window upon.
Your life will be forfeit.
A Future Diary.
Everything I've seen.
No.
Everything I'm going
to see is already here.
Recorded for posterity.
Every little detail about
what my day has in store.
I'm telling ya, man.
His head's swollen up
like a damn balloon.
How does a geek go from
walking with his eyes glued to
his shoes to prancing
around like he
owns the place all of a sudden?
Where's a loser like him
get off acting like a big shot?
Dude's got a hard
wakeup call coming his way.
What the hell?
I don't know, man.
This is the way he takes.
He should be here.
2:12 p.m., outside.
Jocks waiting behind the school.
Thought they'd teach me a lesson
by ambushing me between classes.
They told me that's what
I get for being a poser.
Jerks.
More like dumbasses!
This is awesome!
Keep this puppy in
good shape and
I've basically got a cheat
sheet for, like, everything!
I completely
and totally win at life!
The trail's getting hot.
Uh, Mr. Hiyama?
No offense or nothing,
but number three is bunk.
We never covered this stuff.
Is that a fact?
I could have sworn
we went over it last week.
Yeah.
You know, somehow
I'm just not sweating this.
Go figure.
Why do I even need
to know this crap?
Don't worry, people.
You can always lift the
answers off your phone.
Oh, wait.
Except you can't.
Ha!
Kay... What was
that all about?
Weird.
Excuse me, Miss Gasai, but we
are in the middle of a test.
I'm just keeping
my brain occupied.
I can do two things at once.
Try not to distract
your classmates.
Yuno Gasai.
Straight A student.
Pretty.
Got the whole
school at her feet.
Nah.
Can't be.
I have to be dreaming.
Don't I?
Dead End?
What the hell's going on?
What happened to the future?
Your future.
Don't get them confused.
Hey there Amano.
She knows my name?
You got a dead end, right?
How did you know that?
I saw it coming
a mile away.
It's changed again?
What the hell?!
6:09 p.m., in town.
I escape into a side alley.
I think I lost her.
Will you just hear me out?!
However you're doing this, why
not go and bother someone else!
Get your head around it, man.
There's an explanation.
There's gotta be!
As far as I know
I'm the only one
who's got dibs on
the future, right?
Right?
Okay.
Calm down.
This isn't real.
I'm afraid it is Yuki.
You're kidding me.
You've got one, too?!
Is she going to kill me?
Wait!
My darts!
Don't.
We both know you're
not going to hurt me.
My diary says so.
Tends not to be wrong.
Your diary?
Besides it's not what you think.
You don't have any
reason to hurt me.
He's here.
Who?
The local serial killer.
Known to the other
diary users as Third.
Bad apple.
Third?
He was slated to
take you out of
the running today,
with a machete.
Good thing I've got
the inside track.
This baby's specialty
is keeping tabs on you.
At 6:20 p.m, you're scheduled
to die on the 14th floor.
But, I mean.
You.
All, those entries
are about stuff that I do.
What the?
Well, it wouldn't be much use
to me if it couldn't keep up.
I get the relevant
details on your
future in ten-minute intervals.
The Diary of Future Love.
Ten-minute intervals?
This nut job writes
about me in her diary
every ten minutes on
the frigging dot?
Crazy stalker alert!
In a way, your future kind
of belongs to both of us.
That's it!
I want off!
Silly! Don't start getting
paranoid I'm trying to help!
You'll be the first person
eliminated from the
Survival Game if you
get off on fourteen.
What does that mean?
I...
All Future Diary users are in a
last man standing type of thing.
He's coming for you.
Kay, any second now
she'll start making sense.
If you want my advice,
try not to let your
entries be so topical.
Makes it too easy to track you.
Oh, great idea.
Being on the roof makes
getting away a total cinch!
You know the whole "you can
run but you can't hide," bit?
Kind of fits this
situation to a T.
So, at least up here we
can take in the sunset.
This chick is certifiable.
If I let her call the
shots, I'm dead meat.
This is an ideal place
to confront him.
Are you yanking my chain?!
I do have a plan, you know.
My darts?
That dart's going to
make or break your future.
Hope you're feeling lucky today.
Where are they?
Hide and seek, is it?
I've only got one shot at this.
C'mon, take out your diary.
Remember, a Future Diary
is equal parts weapon
and Achilles' heel.
The fate of a diary and
its user are entwined.
Damn it!
Where the hell are they?!
Destroy his phone.
Destroy him.
Right on the money!
Is that's all we get?
Man, you'd think there'd
be a little bit of blood.
So, what do you say
we grab a bite to eat?
Your mom is out tonight, right?
And you got to have something.
I demand to know
what's going on!
You never said there
were other people
running around with
future diaries!
Neither do I recollect
saying the gift of
future sight was unique to you.
Cheap shot.
Calm yourself.
I've not been duplicitous.
I told you this was a diversion.
What's more, boy,
you stand as its first victor.
Wait. What?
Congratulations, First.
Yeah. Nice work, dude.
Takes some real balls to wipe
out a practiced man-hunter.
I'm looking at the other
diary users, aren't I?
Is that...?
Yuno?
Now that you've all
congregated under the
auspices of my survival game,
permit me to extrapolate
on its rules and purpose.
Let us first consider the
diaries in your possession.
Known, rather quaintly,
as future diaries.
Having begun as ordinary, linear
journals, their relationship to
time has been distorted
to afford you a
window into the future,
up to ninety days.
If I may interject.
Speak your mind, Tenth.
Given your explanation I'm
curious as to how it is I've
witnessed my own diary
rewrite itself multiple times.
The future is subject to change
in response to a user's actions.
Consider, for example, gleaning
foreknowledge of some
imminent personal
catastrophe that is to
befall you down the road.
When the appointed hour of
said catastrophe arrives,
the foreknowledge allows
you to take steps to avoid it,
thus curtailing one future
and inaugurating another.
In other words, the
timeline of which
the catastrophe is
part has been left.
A new future begins; your diary
alters to reflect the change.
Then I have a question.
My diary has changed
without me doing anything.
I mean, I didn't even
know this third creep
was after me to begin with.
None of you is the sole
determinant of your own future,
hence the stakes that render
these proceedings a
test of survival.
Once there is confirmation
that one user
is poised to kill another,
a death sentence will
be entered and the
words dead end sent to
your diary as a warning.
How are we supposed
to know who to
kill when we don't
know who they are?
The identity of your
fellow competitors
can be deduced
from your diaries.
So the first thing
we do is figure out
who everyone is and
take it from there?
Precisely.
Unveiling your opponents
will severely compromise
their position.
Whosoever receives a
dead end warning must
marshal all their
resources to undo it.
Thus discretion is invaluable.
You, First.
Your death at the hands
of Third was written in stone.
But miracle of miracles,
you reduced the verdict to
mere scribbles in the sand!
Should we owe this more
to cunning than luck;
you may well be my champion.
In any event,
without question your
beginnings bode propitiously.
But, what if the cunning
didn't exactly come from me?
Lo!
He who weathers the
vicious onslaught
shall win a throne
incomparable!
Indeed, he will succeed me.
Bearing the mantel of
space-time as its reborn god!
Look around you,
eleven only remain.
Henceforth, consign
mercy to the outlands
of your warrior's heart and vie
for control of the universe!
First things first,
you might say.
Well put.
A pleasant day
to you, o' favored one.
You'd better stay alive long
enough for me to kill you.
Bye-bye, First.
Best of luck to you.
Wait I, uh.
Fear leaves an aura about you.
It sounds like this game
should be interesting
hunting down a kid
with your skills.
It... it wasn't skill!
Easy, kid.
I'm going to be
watching over you.
You poor little monkey.
Please! I...!
I declare this
meeting adjourned.
This is insanity.
There's just no
other word for it.
Don't worry, Yuki.
It'll be okay.
Yuno's here to protect you.
I'll do whatever it
takes to keep you safe.
Cause that's how
much I love you.
♪ closing song ♪
Today's your
lucky day, my friend!
You, sir, have
been chosen to be
one of twelve Future
Diary Users!
Witness.
Okay.
You give me no choice.
Wait, no, no, no!
I'm not!
Alrighty then, seems you kind
of have a problem listening.
Let's try this again: this time
without the hack-n'-slash.
This is a log of your
homicidal conquests, is it not?
Your Murder Diary?
Well, you'll be happy
to know I've added
some killer new features to it.
How did you get
your hands on that?!
It's what I do.
All evidence must be destroyed!
Will you stop that
and listen to me!
Moral of the story.
Some prospective players take
more finessing than others.
Sorry, Third.
That's what you get
for being such
a paranoid pain in the butt.