Come on, damn it!
Open!
This is a nightmare.
I've had better days.
Crazy bitch is trying
to kill us, isn't she?!
Speaking optimistically
I'd say we've got half an hour
until this place is filled
to the rafters with gas.
So yes, she's trying to kill us.
Dinner time, love.
Wakey wakey.
I made your favorite; beef
stew with extra carrots, yummy.
My man needs his strength.
Come on, ah.
♪ opening song ♪
Goddamn it!
This is bullshit!
We just stand here and croak?!
Well I'm not going to go
quietly, I can tell you that!
Keep your shirt on, my friend.
Believe it or not,
as bad as things look,
I don't think we're
out of options.
Knock it off you're going to
break every tooth in
the guy's mouth!
What?
That's hurting him!
How can you be
so freaking clueless?!
You're supposed to be his girl!
Supposed nothing.
I am.
Tell her, darling.
I know it's intense,
but this is home for a while.
We're safe from the
cops here and the other
Diary Users can't
get to us, either.
This is the only way to
reach our happy ending.
I'm all ears, Nancy Drew.
You got a plan?
I suggest we wait a
little longer before you
start blogging your last
will and testament.
There's a lot going on here.
Might as well give
things a closer look.
Time for pee-pees.
Uh-uh!
You're nuts if you think
I'm going to watch this!
Alrighty.
Here goes, off with the undies.
Don't you do it!
Testing, testing.
1 2 3.
Afraid the gig is up.
Before you cut me off,
answer me this.
Having tea with a pair of
skulls up there, per chance?
Excuse me?
You should know
me better than that.
You think I've been
collecting moss since you
two appeared to slip the
surly bonds of Earth?
I went to your house.
Thought it would
be a good idea to
take a second look at that pit.
Good thing...
Cause this go round I hit
pay dirt, so to speak.
Bodies.
Funny thing, though.
There were three of them;
two with heads missing.
Hewn like firewood.
Quite recently.
Now you tell me if it's all that
big of a stretch to assume
you're toting them
around like tchotchkes.
You woke them up!
My parents were sleeping
and you woke them up!
I am many things, but not
disrespectful of the dead;
I didn't just leave them
exposed to the elements.
You put them back
where you found them?
Cut the chit chat and
get on with it already!
Relax...
I'm trying to get
to the bottom of things.
There's still something
about this that doesn't fit,
not matter how I slice it.
Help a guy out
on this one, Yuno.
We've got three corpses
laid to rest in your backyard.
Two sans craniums;
one fully intact.
Let's assume two are
your parents, as you say.
Fine.
Who's contestant number three?
You do know, right?
Tell you what, leave it for now.
Let's negotiate.
You're all dead.
Unless you're cool
with me keying
the fuzz in to your
backyard spa.
You'll nix the gas
and let us out of here.
I mean, mommy and daddy's
corpses taking a dirt nap while
you play house
with their skulls,
you want that on the DL, right?
If you're trying to tick
her off, I think it worked.
Nice, dude.
Now she's going to
ignore us as we die.
I'm at full bars.
Better give me an answer.
You're so random.
What are you talking about?
I'm happy to repeat what's at
stake if you need clarification.
At stake?
Hey, pookie.
Uh...
Your buddies are kind
of weirding me out.
Radio silence, people.
Wait!
No, no, no, no!
I...
Fantastic.
Quite a selective memory.
Rather literally in
this case, I'm afraid.
Aw shit!
What'd she do?!
The gas is coming
out full throttle!
You crazy bitch!
I swear to god.
Snap out of it... Talk
some sense into this nut!
This isn't...
I'm not one of these people;
this isn't how I should go!
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
I'm going to die!
Screw this.
I'm posting my will!
Don't try to sell me anymore
of your optimism bullshit!
There's always a workaround.
Always.
What the hell is this?
Came out of left field.
My phone has apparently
just become one of those, uh...
"Welcome, apprentice." Is this
somebody's idea of a joke?
Okay, according to this I'm
an apprentice diary user!
Come again?
Look!
I'm not yanking ya!
My phone totally
tells the future now!
Anybody else here think
this is totally surreal?
You're going to hoist
me on your shoulders
so I can get out
through the vent!
Umm.
What's a Kousaka Kick?
"I rock?"
This is crazy.
Well it's a better
plan than mine was.
I say go for it.
What've we got to lose?
Wait, what?
--Yeah!
What is that?
Coming loose?
Give me a second.
I'm not James Bond.
I take that back.
I'm awesome.
Part one, done.
Here, take this it's heavy.
Gotcha.
Alright, 007... Recap.
Find your way to the
surveillance room,
Yuno's bound to
have Yuki there with her.
All over it.
Wait a sec.
There's another
diary user nearby.
Kousaka...
Kick!
Yo!
Take notes, people.
That is how you
make an entrance!
And what do we have here?
Ugh!
Seriously, what do you
have against clothes?!
Over here!
Whoa, dude!
Psycho twat managed
to catch you?
Tell me...
Have we met?
Don't even try to
stand there and act
like you don't remember
me, sweet cheeks.
I'm twelve distinct
kinds of badass.
Take it in, ladies.
What's your name?
Did someone hit
you on the head?!
Kousaka?
Hinata.
What's with my voice?
Oh no...
All I wanted was to look
at the stars with her.
She drugged me.
She had to have.
I'm sorry, sweet pea;
I know it's not very pleasant.
I have to do what I can
to protect us till July 28th.
I tried to get away, didn't I?
I'd have done something if
there'd ever been the
opportunity, but...
Slumber party's over, babe.
Cash it in.
My phone now gives me the
pertinent skinny about
what's going to happen.
Like, in what ways
I'll be amazing.
Are you trying to tell me
you're one of the diary users?
How did Kousaka get
his hands on a diary?
So, it's a safe bet
you're here to eliminate us.
I'm here to save his dumb ass.
How are you going to do that?
Think I'll keep the specifics to
myself, but I'm getting him
and Hinata out of here
whether you like it or not.
It says so.
And I got to say, it's
pretty awesome when all you
need to be the hero is
a list of instructions, right?
Uh-uh!
Don't pass out on me!
Don't you worry.
You'd better be
rocking it, Kousaka.
There's an easier way.
Back off and I'll take them out
of here without
kicking your ass.
Less you want to go mano a mano
with the Kousaka King Diary!
Fine...
I give up.
Your majesty needs the keys
to his kingdom, I assume?
Do what?
One of them
unlocks Yuki's shackles.
The other unlocks the control
console, which, by the way,
you'll need if your friends
want out of the gas chamber.
I'm going to toss the
one that controls
the console over to you okay?
And the one for your boyfriend?
It'll sit right there
for the moment.
Insurance while I retrieve dear
old mom and dad, you understand.
If that's not cool,
it's time to speak up.
Otherwise let's do
this nice and easy.
I'd focus on getting my
teammates some fresh air;
the boy can be worried about
once they're in the clear.
It's got to be a trap.
She'd never just
give in like this.
Everything checks out on here.
We have got ourselves a deal.
Break a leg.
Whatever.
She's stalling for
time... has to be!
Oh no!
Don't do it!
She's tricking you!
He's never going
to make it to that key.
And score!
Wake up, Kousaka!
She's going to kill you!
Boyah! The door's
unlocked! You're welcome.
That's music to my ears!
Now commencing
hero deal part deux!
Don't stand
there like an idiot!
Run!!!!
I, I have to do something!
Did, you...
...just hear Kousaka scream
or am I hallucinating?
We should get moving.
But, this wasn't...
How do you suppose
Diary Users fight if they
all have a window
into the future?
Look, I'm begging you
not to kill me, please!
A diary that only tells you
when you've won is a liability.
It's funny, though,
you're a perfect match,
you're both so obsessed with
badass-ness there's no thought
for the times when
you fall a bit short.
Well, what's taking you so long.
Free him like your diary says.
Just be prepared to die
after you've finished the job.
C'mon...
Time's a wasting.
Ugh...
Now what?
Yuki...?
What're you?
You didn't just do, that...
Darling, why?
You and your diary are matched
just as well, sweetheart.
So deal with it.
You're both so fixated on me,
your periphery is shot.
Hinata kicked me the key.
Simple as that.
Three diary users en route.
Not good.
Yuki!
You're alive!
Hinata?!
Please don't!
What are you waiting
for, short round?
Come on!
Let's get out here!
Right.
Sweet pea.
You can't just leave.
If we don't stick together what
chance do we have of making it?
I need you.
Remember?
And it goes without
saying you need me.
Think of what's out there.
We're sitting ducks if we
don't do this as a team!
--Yuki...
--Tune her out.
Hey...
You were going to show
me some stars, mister,
don't think I've forgotten that!
Screw you.
Yuki.
Excuse me, Matron.
Apparently, Kousaka Ouji's diary
has honed in on two other users.
No word yet on who.
I see.
I hope you don't mind, but
I took the liberty of sending in
three of your top
apprentices to help keep
the situation on the
right side of interesting.
Well that should take
care of that, shouldn't it?
Right now, ma'am, Kousaka
is locking horns with Yuno Gasai
but it doesn't look
as though the fight's
going to pan out in his favor.
What have I said about
being a brute, Takeshi?
I'm sorry.
Orin, dear.
Yes, ma'am?
I'm thinking miso and
boiled radishes tonight.
Yeah!
Hey.
Talk to me, Yuki.
How you doing back there?
Fine.
Yeah, well that's sure
as hell not how I'm doing.
I'm sorry.
Stop it; there's no
reason for you to apologize.
She's a nutcase.
And I hate to say it,
but you'll need to be
prepared to see her again.
So that was them just now.
Think we should turn around
and get this over with?
Hell no, right?
What was that all about?
Friends of yours?
You need me whether you
acknowledge it or not,
you misguided bastard.
Because they're coming.
Oh yes; they're coming.
♪ closing song ♪
Ah, nothing like a quick
morning dip to get the old--
Holy shit!
There's a dead
midget in the pool!
It's alive, whatever it is.
Kind, brave sir!
That disarmingly shrill outburst
saved me from the clutches
of death for without
it I would've slept
so long I'd have
needed gills to survive!
Oh.
Okay.
Should you be out here
without your parents?
Never mind that, oh gallant one.
In exchange for
your heroism I am
bound to grant you
a single wish.
Your voice is so weird,
it's like you're a kid, but not.
Wish, please.
Oh...
Well...
Let's see here.
I can't do anything about
your face, so don't ask.
Hey!
For the record I like
my face just how it is!
Whatever.
C'mon, tell me what you
want so we can do this.
Uh...
You're putting me on the spot.
Just ask for what
everyone does...
...the ability to see
into the future.
Are you serious?!
Wait a second; did you
give Yuki his phone?!
I played a very important
part in how he got it.
Awesome!
I want the same
provider he has, then!
Very well.
But before I grant this wish,
you must agree to
undergo a daunting trial
as a test of character!
Eh...
It's not all that far down;
don't even think about it.
You want me to do a swan dive.
Umm.
Hold up.
That'd completely splatter
me from this height.
Ah!
Look who's beginning to spy into
the future like an old
pro wearing a hat.
No kidding?
Like I said, don't even
think about it, just jump!
I'm telling you, if I dive
from up here it'll squish me.
It's the law of
equivalent exchange;
acquisition takes sacrifice!
How is it fair that
I have to die just to
get a peek into the
freaking future?!
Wow, you're either a
cheapskate or a wuss.
Stop whining and do it!
I don't think so!
That was out!
That was a Mulligan!
I get another shot!
Wow...
Respect, man.
Any longer under water and you'd
have needed gills to survive.
I was worried.
That was a...
Hey, is this your phone?
Dream?