Was it really so much to
ask that I get to spend
one single day in bliss
with the man I love?
Mom?
Dad?
Hey.
What's wrong with
the two of you?
Why aren't you waking up?!
I don't want to be alone!
Don't leave me!
We could be a family
if we got married.
Hey, Mom.
Hey Dad.
I'm home.
Yuki said he was going
to head out as soon as he
turned in that
dumb survey for class,
so I waited around for him.
But he must've
slipped out of the
room when I wasn't
paying attention.
Don't worry.
I'll bring my future husband
home to meet you
two soon enough.
Help me, please.
Yuki.
This is how it has to be.
I'm sorry.
This world isn't big
enough for the two of us.
Now I can have
more time with Yuki.
I want to see him.
I want to see Yuki.
So that happened!
I sure hope you're ready to
take the other Yuno's place.
What do you mean?
We should keep this on
the down-low from Deus.
Along those lines.
I'm going to lock away part
of your memory for now.
Her phone.
Can I use it like the
one that I have?
Knock yourself out kid!
It'll tell you the
exact same stuff,
but hey whatever floats
your boat, am I right?
Either one is boss enough
to help you win this thing.
Why, to become a god?
I couldn't care less about that.
Sounds like someone's
still got Yuki on the brain.
Sure you're not
just going to try and off
yourselves together,
like the last time around?
But why?
Why'd you do it?
Oh, darling, it's just
water under the bridge.
Dammit, why'd
you kill yourself?!
This place's getting nuttier
than a bag full of cats.
I hope you don't mind if
we speed things up a little bit.
♪ opening song ♪
Yuno!
Aw, cut her some
slack there, hotshot.
That girl was in a pretty gnarly
headspace after she figured out
her parents were down for
the count and she lost you, too.
Still, it all would've
been hunky-dory.
But a certain someone
had to get all nosy and
take a peek in the room full
of decomposing parent.
If that third corpse
had never been found,
nobody would've ever
come to the conclusion
that the original Yuno
Gasai had left the building.
Second could've opened
the bank vault for you with her
retinal scan, but thanks
to that smoking umbilical cord,
you were sure she
wasn't the real McCoy.
Poor thing's been trying
her damnedest to play the game
like she did the first time,
but it just didn't pan out.
A little sympathy, bro.
Anyhoo, this is
the end of the line.
The Causality Hall.
So why?
Why did you want me dead?
What do you mean?
Stop playing dumb!
You know damn well
what I'm talking about!
Here's a question for you, baby.
Why did you say the two
of us should die together?
You said to me
that you didn't want
to be god if it meant you
had to kill me, darling.
You wanted to die at my side.
So I did.
But you promised me.
You swore to kill me at
the end and win the game.
Don't you know?
I could never kill you.
And that's okay!
But if that's how you feel,
you need to be dead!
Think about it!
If one of us doesn't take
Deus's place, the world's
going to end and
then everybody loses.
It's a big responsibility
but I don't mind!
You'll die, of course but it'll
mean I get the power to go back
to the start and play the
game with you for a third time!
You would hack me to
death for a damn replay?!
Both of us dying doesn't
make any sense, that's all.
If you don't want to kill me,
then I respect your decision.
But if that's the case, you got
to take one for the team.
If you play for a third time,
you're going to have to
kill everyone all over again!
That sounds a
whole lot better than
letting the entire
world come to an end.
If you won the game,
you'd understand.
Hell, what do you
think our world
is but a
gigantic chessboard?
And every last one of
us is a faceless pawn.
And you know
you're not one to talk
about killing people
my big murderous Yuki.
I guess it's about
time to say...
Goodbye.
You're insane.
You're out of your mind,
you know that, right?!
What do you expect of me, huh?!
I'm trapped inside
a madhouse of a
world that never
lets me just be with you!
Yuno was right.
I murdered people
to get what I wanted.
I'm no better than she is.
But whatever goes down
after that is on your head.
So own it.
Uryuu after all this
killing, there's a life.
I want to save!
Not as visceral as
chopping off his head,
but it's probably safe to assume
he's out of the running now.
Are you ready to take the
throne for a second time?
Ladies and gentlemen!
We have ourselves a win!
What was that about?!
How come the future's
changing now?!
I love you.
He's alive!
Yuno!
Maybe I'm nothing
more to you than a
good time to be thrown away.
Please don't
come up here Yuki!
But I...
I really cared about you!
Your heart knows
I'm telling the truth!
No.
Yuno!
I'll save you,
I swear it on my life!
Wait!
It's you!
Dying is for pussies!
Uryuu!
Looks like I saved
your ass yet again!
Hey, no fair!
You were supposed to
be dead by now!
You think you're so slick, huh?!
Let's see you dodge all of this!
Helping Second win
the game, are you?
That's messed
up don't you think?
You watch your damn mouth!
You're not even supposed
to be alive right now,
so you don't get an opinion!
Guess you missed.
Now I get it!
Deus gave you some mojo!
Geez!
A little slow on
the uptake, ain't you!
It's time to go!
We're off to the past,
you chumps!
And away they go.
Well, what do we do?!
We can't just let them escape!
You want to follow them, huh?
Damn straight.
Sounds like you grew
some balls there, kid.
Aw, what the hell.
It's not like I've got
anything better to do.
C'mon!
Yuno!
I won't let you do it!
What a view.
Owe...
Damn.
I got to work on my landings.
Wait a minute.
Didn't you die
detonating your bomb?!
Uh-uh.
Deus had another plan.
After all I've lost I got
my humanity back.
Nishijima.
He saved you?
Hold onto your ass.
It's about to get weirder.
Excuse my, caution,
but we needed privacy.
From Murmur.
Sure, whatever.
I have a question for...
Be still for once.
I hereby bestow upon you
half of my divine power
and knowledge of the cosmos.
Huh?!
What the hell?!
Your hatred of
religion is absolute.
Who better with whom
to share a god's boon?
Murmur's meddled
in the workings of my
game for far too long,
giving Second an advantage
that tipped the
scales unfairly...
Now you will balance them anew.
I believe this Murmur to hearken
from the first
incarnation of my game.
Huh?!
She does not serve me.
Her true master is Second,
who became a god in
another timeline.
You shall be my ace
in the hole, as it were.
Forgetting all of this until
the appointed hour.
Deus wouldn't let me die.
I guess he needs me alive
to clean up his messes for him.
Can't complain, though.
It does let me dish out a
little more whoop-ass.
Kay, then.
Where are we?
Damned if I know.
I was too busy tailing
them through time
to check out the
road-signs, you know?
It's today.
I mean, it's July 28th.
Really.
Two years ago, to the day.
I was still in grade
school back then.
Probably just a fluke.
I don't think of Murmur as
the "planning ahead" type.
Hey...
Check it out.
Since we went back
in time to get here.
That makes this the third
incarnation of the world.
Thinking about it
kind of blows my mind.
Don't let it throw you too hard.
I didn't bring you back
here just to puss out.
Yuno 1.0 plans to kill the
third incarnation of herself
and take her place, buying
herself another go-round of the
game with this world's unwitting
schmuck version of you.
You came here to stop her.
Remember that.
She's going to kill the third
Yuno two hours from now!
We've jumped back to a time
before the new god was selected.
That means the survival
game is still chugging along.
Your diary says that
Yuno arrives at 2:36.
It looks like we
got to the party first.
"Party," huh?
One where she's
going to kill me.
Maybe but that doesn't matter.
I have to protect this world's
innocent Yuno from
the first one.
Hey, just look
on the bright side.
The bitch hasn't killed you yet.
Please, darling, why won't
you just come home already?
I can't take another
day alone with that girl!
Why did we adopt her?
If you're never going to be here
for her, why'd we even bother?!
He hung up.
He doesn't care about
me in the slightest.
But neither do you.
Look at you.
Do you have any idea
why you're such a failure?
Why you can't do anything right?
Mommy's hurting worse
than anything,
and you stare up
at me like it's my fault!
All I need is someone to give a
damn can't you do
that for Mommy?!
I'll help, Mommy.
I promise.
You hate me.
You say you don't,
but I can see it in your eyes.
I'll bet you curse
the very day I was born.
No I don't.
I love you.
No.
You've despised me ever since
the day we brought you home.
You purposely disobey me because
you know how it wounds me!
I know you do!
Mommy, no I would never
do anything to hurt you!
Why am I even here?
You don't need me, and your
father, he's never needed me.
What am I doing,
living in this prison?
What horrible thing did
I do to get sent here?
My whole life is a mistake.
Your silence means
you agree with me!
Don't be sad.
Mommy.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry your mother
is so worthless.
This is goodbye.
I'm sorry, Yuno.
No, wait.
Come back.
Please don't go!
This is the world of
two years ago.
Mom and Dad are
still alive in this one.
Along with everyone else.
Yeah... Well, don't
make yourself at home kid.
Enough gawking.
Let's get down to business
before those two arrive.
Know you this, Funatsu.
We are here to give assistance
to the souls of the weak.
That must never be forgotten.
You're right, Lady Tsubaki,
a thousand pardons.
Have you any wisdom for
the Founder?
Indeed I do.
Tell him to act with all
due prudence while he is away.
And remind him to
only drink in moderation.
As he knows.
I will be observing
him from afar.
Very well.
I take my leave of you, Milady.
"Watching him
from afar," my ass.
If she had second sight
she would never let me
within two hundred feet
of her parents' car.
Pardon me, how are
the preparations
coming along Mr. Mayor?
Better than even I had expected.
Holon's capacity for
analysis is phenomenal.
Putting the finishing
touches on these
Future Diaries should
take no time at all.
I'm pleased to report
that the second
and third Holon units
will soon be operational.
As you know, sir,
that will triple the
amount of processing
power at our disposal.
Good.
Very good.
Then the testing of
prototypes will continue apace.
"Look upon my works,
ye mighty, and despair!"
This should prove
an amusing experiment.
Now we need but
choose which players
to toss into the crucible.
Huh.
Not a single car in the garage.
Are her rich-ass folks
out for the night?
Just beyond this door.
According to my diary,
that's where Mr. and Mrs. Gasai
keep the third
Yuno locked up.
Hey, don't get involved
with this one, you hear me?
Why is that?
I don't need you making
this any more complicated.
Serious.
Cause I'm not looking to
actively court trouble, dig?
You're only here to put
Yuno 1.0 in her place.
I'll just look.
I've got to make
sure she's okay.
Yuno?
That odor.
What is it?
You see?
She's alive.
Now let's jet.
The smell's going
to make me gag.
Hey!
What the hell?!
Wait this is straw.
She was eating the tatami
mat, and choked on it!
Yeah, I need an ambulance ASAP.
A friend of mine ate
something she shouldn't
have and now I think
she's choking.
Come on!
I don't know.
The Gasai residence,
in district 1.
Please, just get here quickly.
Good!
What did I say to you?!
What'd we just
frigging talk about?!
I don't care!
I had to help her.
I know this isn't my
world but she's still Yuno.
I can't write her off.
I can change this
world's future to save her.
God, you're such an idiot.
Yuno.
I'm not letting you kill her.
Got to get up
pretty early in the
morning to get
something past your diary.
It sees Dead Ends
coming from a mile away.
So I brought you
a little surprise.
I think you're going to get a
kick out of these
familiar faces.
Oh my god.
Mom!
Dad!
Well, now that we're all here.
Let the death begin.
Don't do this.
Time to go!
Why the hell are
we running away, Ninth?!
Those are my
Mom and Dad down there!
Don't be stupid!
Those two weren't
your parents, okay?!
The Mom and Dad
you knew are dead!
But they!
Dammit, Ninth!
Take me back!
I've got to get
them out of there!
I'm not going
to lose them again!
Stop squirming around,
you idiot!
Put me down, now!
Put you down, huh?!
What the hell did we
travel back in time to do, kid?!
Save Yuno?! Or save
the new one on my back?!
Or maybe save your folks!
Make up your mind!
Why're we here?!
♪ closing song ♪
Got a problem, feel alone?
Just call me on the telephone!
Hey, party people!
It's time for some
counseling, live on the air!
Yours truly, the
great and powerful Dr. Murmur,
is on the line,
so if something's bugging
you give me a call!
Yeah?
What's your damage?
I'm listening so go nuts!
Uh.
Hello Doctor.
I'm a housewife whose husband
keeps coming home
later and later.
You should catch up on TV shows,
since you don't have to share
the remote with anybody.
Bam.
What's your damage?
I'm ready,
so knock yourself out!
Hi.
It's me again.
Actually, my husband
isn't coming home
at all not for days
at a stretch.
What's worse, he won't
even answer his phone!
Dr. Murmur, you don't you don't
think he's avoiding me, do you?!
Pretty much, yeah.
Take yourself a nap.
Could be a while.
Bam.
Dr. Murmur speaking.
What's your major malfunction?
Me again, sorry!
The nap thing didn't work!
Look, my husband's not
coming home, ever!
And my daughter's a
hopeless ingrate!
She hardly ever listens
to a word I say,
and when she does,
it's just to give me backtalk!
And she won't study!
Not that her grades
are bad,
mind you but they
could be better!
It's not that I don't
care about her feelings,
but the competition for the good
schools is getting insane.
If she doesn't give it her all,
she won't make the cut!
I only push her because I care!
Hello?
Get a hobby, sister.
I suggest social drinking.
Bam.
Okay talk to me, home-girl,
I know it's you again.
It probably has
nothing to do with it
but that problem child of
mine is adopted.
My husband and I
weren't able to have kids,
not that we tried
nearly often enough
for my liking but
that's a whole other call.
Our folks are pretty
loaded, so we were
hoping for a boy to
inherit the family business.
But we adopted a girl.
Go figure.
You should have
the birds-and-the-bees
talk with your husband.
Yup.
Wow, that was pretty fast!
So, what did he think?
You have to help me, Doctor!
I'm in serious
trouble over here!
Could you be a
little more specific?
Just give me one
morsel of good advice!
I'm only going to say it once.
You ready?
Yes!
I'm not a doctor.
I'm really just an intern here.
See ya!
Bam.
Well, that's all the
time we have for tonight!
This is Dr. Murmur,
signing off!