Mr. Mayor!
Closing the orphanage
would be political napalm!
If we turn those kids
out into the street,
the media will rip us a new one!
Well, Balks?
What do you have to say?!
What can one say?
To think of the friendships
that sustain those
children being torn asunder!
Weep though I may, the
orphanage stands accused
of sheltering the perpetrators
of the tower bombing
which I know in my
very bones to be true!
I beg your pardon?
The dark seed of sedition
has taken root in that house,
and we must needs dig it up!
You can't prove that!
So we wait for another
attack on our city?!
I swear to you!
I love the children of Sakurami
as though they were
mine own kin!
That goes double for the waifs
that call the orphanage home!
I know you would never
throw those blameless souls
to the wolves for mere
political self-preservation!
I cannot allow the
city's orphans to
sleep under the same
roof as those terrorists!
Haven't they... haven't they
been through enough?!
What objections could
you possibly have to
safeguarding our
city and our children?!
I can't fathom such
thinking, so explain it.
Those who agree with me, stand.
The yea's have it.
The orphanage known as Mother's
House will be shut down...
...effective immediately.
♪ opening song ♪
So, you wanna give
First and Second
the old heave-ho
from the game, huh?
There's been no sign
of them for five days.
They haven't even
deigned to show up here,
in the safety
of Deus's presence.
It should be clear to all that
they refuse to participate.
Five whole days!
Deus's condition worsens
with each passing hour.
He doesn't have time for them
to "run down the
clock," as it were.
I believe you're right.
Such stalling goes against
the spirit of this game.
According to what
Nishijima tells me,
Mother's House is really
taking it on the chin.
I bet it's that windbag,
Eleventh.
He's trying to take down
three Keepers all at once.
Ambitious.
Who is this guy?
In light of these facts,
First and Second leave me
with no choice but
to remove them from--
Not yet!
Geez, skip out on
a couple of meetings
and you're public
enemy number one.
About time.
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Eleventh.
I mean...
Mayor of Sakurami!
What do you think I was up to
for the last five days,
huh, Cueball?!
Fair enough.
It seems the remaining players'
identities have been
brought to light.
The need to obfuscate
your appearances
within this realm
no longer applies.
The prize of
godhead will be mine!
How did you find me?
I want to know.
You make it sound
like it was difficult.
It was child's play.
I spent the last five days
right under your nose.
sitting in the lobby
of Sakurami City Hall.
My diary takes note of
everything around me,
and City Hall is a pretty
happening place!
You wouldn't believe how
much info I soaked up,
just zoning out in a chair.
Right before the vote was held
about whether or not to shut
down the orphanage you gave
a speech to the other bigwigs.
That's when you laid it on
thick, because you knew the
measure wasn't going to
pass through the council
unless you guilted them
into total submission.
What do you think, Yuno?!
Did I sound like a badass?!
Oh, you were perfect!
Like something right
out of a movie!
Well, I did have a script,
so I guess the
comparison's pretty spot-on!
You hit it outta the
park with this, Yuno!
I just, threw together a
general outline you're the one
who actually had
to pull it off, darling.
Besides, we've only
slowed Eleventh down a bit.
We haven't stopped him.
Stopped him from what?
You know.
Going after Eighth's Propagation
Diary, which will be way
easier now that
their home base is kaput.
The funding for Mother's House
comes straight outta City Hall.
And I'm pretty sure
Eighth is renting
her diary's server
on the town's dime.
If the orphanage shuts down,
then all its assets
revert back to the city.
Yeah but, what could a
guy like the mayor of Sakurami
possibly want with a
secondhand server, anyway?
He probably wants
to have his own minions.
What?!
If he pulls that off,
we're all screwed!
It's a good thing I wrote this.
Because there's always a sequel.
All you have to
do is stick to some
scripted cues again,
and win over Eighth.
Yuki, what's up?
I just don't know
if I can pull this off.
That's all.
What the hell?!
I'm not gonna
let you be a quitter.
My baby's going to kill the
rest of those diary users
then send me off to the
grave and become god.
You promised to make
your parents happy.
And I seem to remember
you promising
that to the girl who's lying
on top of you as well.
So suck it up.
You're finished
when I say you are.
She's right.
There's no turning back.
My baby's gonna
do his very best.
So that's it, then.
I win, or I perish.
What did you say?!
You heard me, Officer.
Eleventh is John Balks, a.k.a.
the mayor of this
podunk little backwater.
But that's impossible!
But wait, there's more.
It sounds like old First and
Second are gunning for him.
Now how much would you pay?
What's the matter?
I just got out of a
meeting with the police chief.
As of this morning, I'm on
the mayor's security detail.
That's some bad fucking luck!
So, whose side are you going to
take when the shit hits the fan?
This is no laughing matter.
So spare me the snark!
"Please forgive my insolence."
There, that do the trick?
Dug up anything on Second yet,
or do I got to do all the work?
Uh... We're waiting
on the lab-work for
one of those bodies
from her backyard,
but they bounced us back
positive IDs for the other two.
They belong to
Ushio and Saika Gasai.
Yuno's mother and father.
They came from money,
both sides built their
fortunes in the banking biz.
A match made in yuppie heaven.
By all accounts, they were
desperate to have children,
but they never did.
Uh... Didn't you just
call them her folks?
Akise's off trying to get to the
bottom of that very question.
We have two enigmas
on our hands.
Yuno and that corpse.
The plot thickens, huh.
Yuno just flashed the signal.
Is everyone all set?
Just so we're clear on this...
I don't trust you any farther
than I can throw you.
I could say the same.
But for the moment I think
it would behoove us
both if we worked together.
Eleventh has backed Eighth
into a corner with the closing,
and Yuno and I don't want him
getting his hands on the
Propagation Diary.
Don't forget, we did
you guys a solid already.
Helping with your diary, like we
did, was a sign of good faith.
Let's go over the plan again.
Just as one plus two
plus eight equal eleven,
Eighth and Second
and I are teaming up
to cancel out Eleventh.
I'll start things off by
heading down to the road.
Once I'm there, I'll use
my Indiscriminate Diary
to halt the mayor's caravan.
Then, when the time is
right, we unleash a cloud
of sleeping gas on
his little entourage.
That'll be the signal for the
attack to go into full swing.
Orin, you'll use your diary
to monitor the status of all the
orphans and direct
their movements
during the attack phase.
I got it covered.
Speaking of covered.
Taro will hang back
to defend Eighth
and make sure I don't
try anything funny.
That Copy Diary of yours
is pretty handy, Taro.
You've harnessed the power of
Yuno's phone, and can keep
tabs on me in
ten-minute intervals.
Listen up.
If you try and pull
a fast one, I will take--!
Take me out?
Yeah, I know.
Everything's gone
according to Yuno's script.
Hey...
Have one.
They're not poisoned or
anything, so just go to town.
Are there enough?
Uh-huh.
I know you're not the sneaky
bastard Ta thinks you are.
I was at Omekata and I
saw how you acted.
Eighth seems like
a pretty nice lady.
How does she deal with all this?
Aw, she's awesome.
She doesn't even care about
trying to become god.
She only plays
this game 'cause of us.
We orphans have
been begging her to win,
so she goes along with it.
Because she loves us.
And we love her right back,
that's why we're here.
I know she's gonna
make it a better world if
she gets the chance
to be the new god.
Anyway.
Thank you.
That was very nice of
you to share your onigiri.
I'm glad you like it!
Look, Orin.
I don't think
you should be here.
It's gonna get bad and if
something happens to
Eighth, then you...
Nothing's gonna happen to her.
I won't let it.
Okay, then.
Time to do this!
A roadblock?
Oh shit!
It's an ambush!
More of them are
coming down the hill!
Take them out!
Wait... that's Yuki!
This makes no sense.
That boy said he spent
the better part of a week
in City Hall he should
know what our plans are.
Why is he attacking us?
Megumi!
There's a cop just right
of the smoke cloud!
Jun, pull back!
I'll be damned!
First's plan is working
just like he said it would!
And he hasn't
pulled anything shady.
Guess I was
worrying for nothing!
What the?!
Guys!
There's something on the car!
Huh?!
No way!
What'd that guy do to my phone?!
I can't connect to the server!
I knew I'd have to deal with
Eighth at some point or another,
so I had my
car outfitted with the
latest tech for the
jamming of cell phones.
They can do that?!
You sold us out!
Hurry up!
You got to bust that
thing on top of his car!
You were right.
You traitorous bastards!
She was just a little kid!
We formed this
alliance to hand you to
Eleventh on a silver platter.
That's the one reason we stooped
to work with you amateurs.
We didn't come out here
to ambush the mayor.
We trusted you!
And this is how you repay us?!
We came to murder Eighth!
Your lives weren't
taken in vain.
At the end of this
game once I'm a god.
I'll bring you back.
You haven't won the game yet,
you little backstabber!
Kamado, you got to run for it!
Please, just go!
Get in the car now!
We can break through!
C'mon, baby!
We can use this to chase them!
Eyes on the diary!
Take it!
It looks like things
are gonna go our way.
The Diary says we'll
catch up to them
after I shoot out their tires.
Thanks in advance.
Huh?
How could they
have figured it out?!
I, I made sure there was
nothing to test it against!
If Yuki finds out, he'll...!
Don't look so worried,
Yuno we're in this together.
I'll never let you go again.
I promise.
You monster!
I lost all of my children
today because of you!
Spare me the theatrics; I know
the score they were lying in
wait to spill my blood, so drop
the righteous indignation.
But it turns out that your
scheming was all for naught.
Thanks to my diary...
The Watcher.
I will emerge triumphant!
"The Watcher."
Right on schedule.
The fools.
We're gaining on him!
Crap! So they're gonna try
and lose us on the freeway!
Get ready to switch lanes!
Bring me up behind them as close
as you can, all right baby?!
Yuno!
He's depending on me.
I have to shoot the tire
like his diary predicted!
He dodged the shot?!
I'm betting he used his diary to
predict the timing of your shot!
If his keeps track of his
surroundings like mine does,
we might have a problem!
But if it does work like Yuki's,
he only knows what's
happening around him.
Forget the tires I'm cutting
out the middle-man!
Missed me.
Wait so, he can predict what's
gonna happen to himself?!
Dammit to hell!
Give the mayor
the strongest one!
Yeah, that's fair, Deus!
So, he intends to force
us off the road, does he?
That's rather barbaric of
you First, you disappoint me.
Yuno get up.
Are you all right?
We got to kill them
before they get away!
Huh?
You ready to die?
Not today, little girl.
The arrival of
allies will rob you
of the opportunity
to gun me down.
Your men don't frighten me!
I never told you they
were my allies, now did I?
You don't mean!
Akise, what're you doing here?!
Hey, kiddies.
We're all gonna
have us a little chat okay?
You've got the grenade,
so you start.
Hey, I do have an
eye for a good time.
I picked up Sherlock here went
down to the lab and then we used
a police scanner to track
down you party-animals.
They went to a lab?!
Turns out we found a positive
match for the DNA of
contestant number three in
your backyard hobby hole.
Our smoking gun!
Go ahead, Yuki.
Open it up.
No...
It can't be.
I don't get it.
It's something we were
able to track down at the
orphanage where Yuno was
abandoned as a newborn.
Wait....
Are you saying this is?
You figured it out.
That's a bit of Yuno
Gasai's umbilical cord.
Why did they keep that thing?!
We had the lab salvage
whatever DNA they could
from that and
compare it to the DNA
from the mystery corpse
found with Yuno's folks.
And in a delightful
twist to this story the
two samples matched
each other perfectly.
You're a liar!
Yuki, don't listen!
He's lying!
You're telling me that
they were the same?
That's right.
And when I say they
matched, I don't mean the
two samples were taken
from the same family.
Specifically...
Please, Yuki make him stop!
He doesn't know
what he's talking about!
It means that the third body
is none other than Yuno herself.
The real Yuno shuffled off
this mortal coil ages ago.
But, then who is this?
Occam's Razor.
If Yuno is dead,
then that girl is an impostor.
Whoever she is, I advise
you to step away from her.
No!
I'm not an impostor!
I swear it, Yuki!
I can...!
I can explain!
You believe me, don't you?!
Don't you, Yuki?!
We can get through this!
No!
What're you?!
Yuki!
♪ closing song ♪
Thank you for
all the tasty food!
Thanks for not
leaving any leftovers.
Whoa.
I guess we forgot one.
Never seen her before.
Dig in.
Are you sure?
No prob.
Now eat it while it's hot.
Good, huh?
By the way, are you
supposed to be here?
This is an orphanage, you know,
a place for kids who
don't have parents,
or who have them but can't be
with them for some
reason or another.
What are "parents," anyway?
They're, um, the big people
who look out for you
all the time and stop you
from getting into trouble.
Right here.
I guess I've got
someone like that.
Well, tell me
about your parents,
then and don't leave
anything out.
I bet you that they're
really nice to you.
I can tell that much
just by looking.
Nice?
Yeah, Not so much.
So, are they super-weird, then?
How do you know?
They're super-duper-weird!
Like, weird, weird?!
Weird squared, even!
That's a lot of weirdness.
And you don't
know the half of it.
Of course they're weird.
Look what they've
got you wearing.