Yuno Gasai.
It appears I have my
work cut out for me.
"Just think of it
as an opportunity
to prove the cut of your jib!"
Good advice.
"Don't get so cocky you
let your guard down.
You're squaring off against
two players here who
have proven the cut
of their jib several times."
You won't be able to get
the drop on them easily;
they can use their diaries in
tandem to blackout your options.
Oh, yeah.
Something else to consider.
Your diary is just
this side of being a joke.
"Hyper Vision Diary"?
More like, 'poor
little boo-boo's
three-entries-per-day
picture-bo ok.'
Morning. Noon. Night.
Yeah... Seriously...
Good luck with that."
Three windows
of opportunity a day.
That's two more
than you need to win!
If I can take the lovebirds
down with one stone,
so much the better.
Mom and Dad must be avenged.
Ha!
Who am I kidding?
I don't give a
damn about my folks!
I'm in this for sweet,
sweet victory,
and these two need
to be taken out.
That's all.
♪ opening song ♪
Wow... Is it me or
is that a lot of food?
Eat some salad!
I made it myself!
Our budding little sous chef
was so eager to lend a hand.
Nice...
Suck up.
Sorry, gang.
I've got to take this.
So what brought you to our
humble abode, short stuff?
My mommy and daddy have
to work late for a long time.
They wanted me
to come stay here.
Uh...
Well, that was
very thoughtful of them.
The lettuce is shy, so we've got
make it dance with the cucumber.
Throw a couple of
special tomatoes into
the mix and we've
got ourselves a hoedown.
Grab your partners, do-si-do.
Not that one.
What is that all about?
Come on, Eat it!
Wait, something's not right.
This tomato's off.
It's heavier than
when I washed it.
Water retention?
Don't be cute.
I'm telling you I think
something's wrong.
You shouldn't eat it.
Better safe than sorry.
Observant little minx,
isn't she?
I think she might be
a little paranoid.
Whoa, why'd it do that?
Seriously?
Second is on alert,
but I wonder about First.
Not that it matters
one way or the other.
I'll get my chance.
Hope you're not mad at me
for throwing out the salad.
I mean, you put so
much work in to it.
That really sucks.
Naw.
You didn't want anyone
to get a tummy ache.
Well, it's kind of my thing to
look after people I care about.
That's why I'm going to
keep a close eye on you.
Thank you.
So adorable.
Oh, she is good.
I just might be in love!
The real measure of
an electric shock's intensity
isn't the voltage.
Currents as low as
110 volts can be fatal
under the right
circumstances.
And plain old table salt
ratchets up tap
water's conductivity.
Double, double,
toil and trouble.
Fire burn and cauldron bubble.
Really? Again?
But I haven't done anything?
Why does the
future keep changing?
Crap!
There's got to
be another user nearby!
Cut it out!
Wait... Yuno gets electrocuted?!
How the hell is
that going to happen?!
Hey, sis.
Can I take a bath with you?
Oh...
Do you need help?
I promise not to splash.
I'm not going to make
it to her in time!
C'mon, think!
Damn it, there's got
to be something!
There's a sweet
irony to this, really.
First will go second.
And Second will go first.
Die!!!
Turbo!
Huh?
The circuit breaker's
been tripped!
Maybe First isn't so clueless.
Are you okay?!
Please tell me
this isn't happening.
He better not be asking me out.
Why'd I have
to give him my info.
What's this about Fifth?
Oh, snap...
Have fun taking
out a toddler, First.
Somehow the image
of you being terrorized
by a half-pint is
hilarious to me.
What gives?
Why's Johnny Law keeping
me in the loop about this stuff?
It's got to be here somewhere.
If the kid's a diary user,
then his diary's
somewhere in this house.
Could be anything
though, couldn't it?
What'd he have on him when
Mom brought him home?
There's a faster
solution to this.
Kill him.
Don't even start!
He's here to kill you.
It's only fair.
He's only a kid!
I don't want a toddler's
blood on my hands!
Look, just cut it out and
help me find his diary!
What if he makes another
move before we find it?
I...
Let's just hope it
doesn't come to that, okay?
It will.
I have to go and
make a number two.
You're not going to get
the better of me that way.
I'm far too clever
for either of you.
Where could a kid
his height reach easily.
Fail.
I figured we'd have a shot
if I combed the places
not mentioned in my diary.
And, bam!
Yeah, that was dumb.
Damn it, I thought I made
myself perfectly clear!
I'm trying to tell you:
it'll be a lot
quicker and easier
if we do it my way.
Put that down!
Mom's going to see you!
What kind of shenanigans are
those two getting up to now?
Beats me.
Hey, let's move to a new stage.
Alright. Hang on.
I need only continue
my infant act a bit longer.
At high noon,
the gloves come off.
If it's not here, I'm completely
dried up on what next.
We're not even close.
So we have confirmation
this was a bad idea,
seeing as he's
never left the house.
Except when mom took
him with her to the store.
You don't suppose he could've...
I mean that's a pretty
risky place to hide.
Hey...
Where'd you go?
I was talking to you.
No point keeping up
appearances now, huh?
Sounds like World War
three down there.
What have you done?!
I'm such an idiot.
You just had to go
with your instincts.
This is exactly the kind of
stupid thing I wanted to avoid!
I'm sorry, Yuki.
I'm so sorry.
Look...
It's okay.
Your heart was
in the right place.
What we need to
focus on now is getting
our hands on that
little brat's diary.
So, chin up.
I can't do it without you.
Yeah?
Something tells me
we don't have a lot of time.
My man needs me.
Besides, find the diary,
and he'll probably
overlook me cracking
his mom's skull.
Alright.
I'm a four year old prodigy.
A hiding place for the
most valuable thing
I own only makes sense
if it's easily accessible,
practically beneath
the awareness
of my opponents,
and most of all consistent.
Where is it?
C'mon. It's staring
us in the face.
Think.
Whoa...!
What the hell?!
Holy crap.
Whatever it is you're doing,
just please don't be murdered!
The corner store
has a delivery service.
I send a package.
I address it to myself.
It's almost here!
Just a second!
Stop him, Yuki!
That's the hiding place!
No you don't!!!
Ha ha!
Now I've got you!
Don't open it!
Excellent.
Yuki! No!!!
Oh god!
Oh god, oh god, oh god!
Hang in there, my love!
Yuno's here for you;
I'll get us out of this!
Victory is mine!
Weren't expecting a lethal
dose of nerve gas, were you?
People who don't
want to die unseal the
package from the
opposite end, you see.
Live and learn, I guess.
Don't be a party pooper.
You going to hole
up in there all afternoon?
Get out here!
Forget about him.
There's nothing you
can do, he's a goner.
Come out and play.
I was probably the one
who killed your parents.
Matter of fact I'm sure of it.
If you want revenge, take me.
He had nothing to do with it.
Aw, that's sweet but I'm
not in this for payback.
Thing is, I've grown
rather fond of you.
Butchery is just
how I express it.
Come out and play!
Fight it all you want, big sis.
You and I both
know we're going to
go at each other like animals.
Fine, then.
Be a bitch.
How about I up
the ante a little?
If you beat me, you get a prize.
The antidote!
We'll keep it simple and treat
this like Hide 'n Seek.
Find me, and you get to save
your stupid boyfriend.
Let the gas overcome you, and,
well I'll be the winner.
Mom. She's
breathing this in.
We have to get her out
of here before it's too late.
I'm not a monster.
I'm hardly going to let Miss
Amano suffer because of you two.
So are we on or what?
Just remember:
breathe shallow or this
stuff will do nasty things
to your insides!
And go!
Don't do it.
There's no way
this isn't a trap.
If you go out there,
he'll be waiting
in ambush with
something terrible.
How very chivalrous
of you to worry about me.
Thank you.
I'll be back with the antidote
before you know it, my darling.
You're crazy.
Doing fantastic, big sis.
But this is just the
start of round one.
How long do you
think you can hold
your breath or is
that a moot point?
Someone's in for a big,
gasping surprise!
Nerves of steel, that girl.
Sheesh.
I'd better find
another hiding place.
I so love it here!
Miss Amano is super nice.
I have a big brother
and sister to play with.
I never much cared
for my other home.
Who needs a dumb
old mom and dad, anyhow?
I'm perfectly self-sufficient.
As First and Second are
about to find out the hard way.
Tell me what's going on outside.
Please.
Damn it. This thing
is useless from in here.
I've got to make it
to the yard somehow.
Not on the first floor.
Meaning...
Uh-oh!
Looks like I'm it!
Bring it.
You've got me good
and cornered, big sis.
But I'm not as easy to
take down as all that.
Oh, no.
What do I have here?
Better luck next time.
Now that's what I
call a shocking victory!
What's happening?!
Explain something
to me, would you?
If the object of
this game is for us
to all slaughter each other,
why do you go to such
lengths protecting First?
You can stop holding
your breath, by the way.
I'm not in this for myself, I...
I protect him out of love.
Aw, then it's just as
well that you lose now.
It's been fun, Yuno.
I'm sorry, Yuki.
Damn it!
Yuki.
I'm guessing... that you
don't understand true love.
Guess not.
Good.
Good for you.
You're...
You are one amazing woman.
Don't worry, it's real.
It's too late to pull a
fast one on you now.
Still, though, is it worth it?
The more you win,
the closer you get to
what's shaping up to
be an ugly stalemate.
Eventually, there'll
be no one left to kill but him.
And then where will you be?
You going to protect the
man you love from yourself?
How is that supposed to work?
What will your love be
worth at the moment of truth?
Sorry, I won't be
around to see it.
Oh, and uh...
Congratulations.
I don't give a damn.
I'll protect my man from
whoever the hell I've got to.
Hang in there, pookie.
The antidote's coming.
A word of advice, kid.
Kill her.
There's only one winner to
this game, so just deal with it.
Push comes to shove,
mercy won't factor in
to how she deals with you.
♪ closing song ♪
So, yeah.
You get to be a diary user
and creatively kill a
bunch of people.
Cool, hey, tell me something.
Are aliens, like, real?
It stands to reason.
If gods are real,
surely aliens have a shot.
Uh...
Tell you what.
I'm in.
But only and I mean only if
you show me a bona fide alien.
I come from beyond the stars.
Take me to your leader.
Behold.
The Mother ship I
have traveled here in.
Ah, neat!
Wow, really drives home just how
insignificant we all are, huh?
Win this game,
and the absolute last thing
you'll ever be is insignificant!
Screw that, I want to
be self-sufficient!
Um, okay then.
Where has my saucer gone?