Big, fat hole in the
ground for my darling Yuki.
Big, fat, hole in the
It's all for you, love.
All of it gets buried for you.
It's the least I...
Okay.
What exactly was I doing again?
♪ opening song ♪
That ought to do it.
Can't believe the bastard's got
me running recon for his mess.
Anybody else and
we'd have words.
Son of a whore!
"Ninth was so sure the
Escape Diary would trump the
Murder Diary that
she dove headfirst
into a showdown with Third."
"She hadn't counted
on her adversary's
knack for
sidestepping explosives."
"No, sir."
Shit!
Not my leg!
"Fortunately, the man
of her dreams came along."
Oh my gosh.
You're Uryuu Minene, aren't you?
You've got to be kidding!
You're, like, that terrorist!
"'Hold it right there,'
he said."
"Unhand me!'"
"No, I can't do that.
I'd rather die than
risk losing you again."
"'You're a liar!
As if I mattered a
hill of beans to you!'"
"'I speak the truth!'"
"'I... I think. I'm in love.'"
"'Keep your distance!
You'll never have her
as long as I breathe!'"
"'Of all the streets
in the all the world,
why'd you have
to pick this one?'"
"'We must run.'"
"'I am done with fear!'"
"'I beg you; do not
cross swords over me!'"
"'But, my darling.'"
"Please, If you truly love me,
you'll put an end to
this bloodshed!'"
"Ask and I will obey.
Never again will I let you go!'"
"And they dashed through
the rain-soaked streets,
Third in hot pursuit."
Romantic, huh?
Mind if I enquire as to what,
precisely, you are reading from?
What, this?
It's called manga.
I'll admit, I get a
kick out of the way
they portray the whole
boy-meets-girl thing.
Real life just doesn't compare.
"'The vermin.
'He's taken what's
rightfully mine!'"
"'Curse his name!'"
"'You shall live
to regret this!'"
Where are we?
An old art school.
Pretty hopping place before the
economy got flushed
down the toilet.
So, uh...
We going to run for the rest of
our lives, or what's the plan?
Beats me.
Till I have an idea
how far ahead his
Diary sees, we're flying blind.
His what?
Forget it.
I've been in this
game for all of three days
and you're already
telling me it's lights out?
I don't think so.
You're dealing with me.
Follow my lead.
Whoa.
There could be
somebody in there.
There isn't.
Trust me; I know
where I'm going.
What is this supposed to be?!
Huh?
It's not like you got
to act mystified.
It's probably just...
I don't know a fashion
design class or something.
Haven't you ever
played dress-up?
What do you think?
If you're about to
blow chunks, please don't.
Take these off.
Hell no.
Take them off!
Not going to happen.
Come on, please?
Just for a sec?
Sorry.
Look, I'm trying to be nice!
This is kind of an emergency!
Does he know where we are?!
Damn it.
My bladder needs to
speak to a lawyer, okay?
You enjoying this?
Stop taunting me.
Pervert.
I don't have a choice.
Sicko.
I'm an officer of the law.
Toilet Trader.
Look, put yourself in my shoes.
A fugitive angle for a pit stop;
one of the oldest slips
in the playbook.
Give me a break.
This is balls.
Don't look at me!
I'm not.
Don't inhale!
Trying not to.
Don't listen.
Can't hear a thing.
You're a lying asshole!
Will you just
concentrate, please?
If we don't get a move-on,
Psycho's going to catch up.
Let's stop back by
the classroom first.
Here.
You're going to
catch your death.
You're sopping wet.
Don't argue.
What are you, my mother?
You're not going to get
very far from this slasher
with pneumonia.
Besides, I can stay handcuffed
to you outside a bathroom stall,
but not while you're changing.
Alright...
You can turn around.
Whoa. Hey...
We found a good look for you.
Hey, if this plays to some sick
childhood fantasy of yours,
to each his own.
But get this straight: all it
is to me is something dry.
Whatever...
You look cute.
Shithead!
Now get over yourself and
help me come up with a plan.
Is it too much to hope for that
you have any weapons?
I have a sonic grenade left
but...
But what?
Hello?
It's... It's, uh...
Well, you know.
My last one.
Well, how about that even
a hard-ass like you can blush.
Get the hell away!
Unless you're a doctor...
Sorry!
Laugh it up.
Sicko.
Sorry.
I just wasn't prepared
to be in this position.
You don't say.
Listen, enough of
this screwing around
I've got to get you downtown.
I'm out of my depth here anyway.
Shut up.
What, are you scared?
Thought you wanted to be a hero?
The only thing
protecting this guy
from us is a
bulletproof vest.
Granted, all my
grenade can do is
buy us a little bit of time.
If it works.
But...
What kind of beats
you listen to when
you're not picking
low hanging fruit?
I'll bet nothing like what
you're about to hear.
I'd love your opinion!
"By their wits, they
escaped unmolested."
What would their next
move be if this were from...
Well, a girly book?
All signs point
toward an elopement.
Their love would blossom
under the sun of freedom.
Aw...
Okay, not romantic but whatever.
I don't do girly.
If you're smart, you'll find
another genre to put me in.
I'm not a trophy for
some douche on a horse.
Right, Murmur?
Enough of that.
When most little girls were
sipping tea with
stuffed animals,
I was scrounging through rubble.
Romance ain't on my bucket list.
Never will be.
I live in the real world.
Not one decorated in pink.
It's called being an adult.
I might be a little early,
but not by much.
Aru and me are going
to catch a movie.
Like friends do.
Hello, my love.
Huh?
Oh, hey.
What are you doing here?
Don't just sit there, silly man.
Don't want the bus to
leave without us, do we?
Excuse me.
I've already got plans with
Akise, if you don't mind.
That's why I'm here.
He told me you'd say that;
but it's fine, I've got this.
Come on.
Let's go.
You know where he is?
Sure do.
"Hello, Gasai.
I apologize..."
"I apologize for the short
notice, but did you know
they're holding free trial
weddings this Sunday?
Yukiteru is itching
to invite you,
but he's really embarrassed,
so I'm relaying the message.
I'll be waiting at the
bus stop on Third, at 10:30."
"Relaying the message."
Wait, what the hell is
he talking about?
But he distinctly told
me to meet him here.
Why would he make up some
story to get Yuno involved?.
Unless the dude's up
to something.
You son of a bitch!
Bet you haven't had
breakfast yet, have you?
Well, have no fear
I came prepared!
I thought a text every
ten minutes was bad.
Now she sends twice as many
and walks me to every class.
Tada! Eh?
I don't even
think there's a word
for how out of control
this is getting.
I would like to introduce you
all to someone very special.
This is Yuno Gasai
My, uh, girlfriend.
Sure, my back was
to the wall at the time,
but I should've just
kept my mouth shut.
I have to find a way
to break it to her.
Except the truth's going
to land me on her bad side.
Here comes the airplane!
I hate my life.
Oh, wowza!
It's right out of a book!
Sure, a book.
One I'd never want to read.
Let's just go back
the way we came.
I'm kind of, I don't know,
out of my element
in a setup like this.
Now that's not fair.
Everyone's welcome.
If you plan to get married
one day, so much the better.
Out of your element.
We're all about young couples!
Thanks!
Kurusu?
See? We're fine.
Let's go sample their
reception banquet options.
Eh?
Is this edible?!
Wow.
Looks Like something
only royalty would eat.
Wanna taste how
the other half lives?
Why not?
Holy crap!
It's actually pretty good.
But, what am I eating?
Like, hamburger?
It's called foie gras.
What is this stuff
that looks like sludge?
That would be caviar.
Hey! Check it out:
I should totally be
wearing a monocle!
Only if I get to wear a tiara.
Oo!
And like an ermine coat!
Who told you I was
in the business of
babysitting snot-nosed
little brats?!
Um, nobody.
They just said this is where
I'd go to try on dresses, maybe.
So now I have to
clothe you as well!
I make dresses for sophisticated
women, not cow-eyed Tinkerbells!
I am an artisan!
Fair anointed youth cares not
for the subtle drape of cloth.
Nor an ageless
cut of quality fabric.
You like cheap crap.
Would the groom
like to try something?
Wha?
You talking to me?
Oh my...
You look like a
lord of the manor.
You think so?
Behold, a woman!
Step out, dear.
Show it off.
Not my usual style,
but what do you think?
Be honest.
You look beautiful.
Am I really?
Well, you're not
so bad yourself.
Okay chins a little to the
left and say "Registry."
Oh man, we are smoking!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Why the hell am
I suddenly into this?!
We're about as far from
a real couple as you can get!
I'm up a creek.
Unless I come clean and tell her
the whole thing's been an act,
she's going to think
this is our life now forever!
Hey, Yuno.
Please don't look
at me right now.
I just can't control myself.
Ma'am?
Would it be possible
to try on another dress?
Guess I don't have to drop
the bombshell right now.
This may sound
kind of weird but I...
Maybe we are a couple
and I'm just too seized up
with whatever the hell's
wrong with me to admit it.
Still, though.
She is crazy.
Yeah...
Definitely crazy.
This is adorable!
If it hadn't been for that.
If I'd never looked
into that damn room.
Would I...
Could I have fallen for her?
Time for the main event.
I'd say you two
look good and ready.
What would you think
about a practice ceremony?
Wait, I'm sorry, what?!
But we're not actually...
Uh, I mean...
Don't be afraid.
No one's going to
force you to do it.
This has been fun.
No need to cap it
off with a ceremony.
Don't want to tempt fate.
It's not the real deal, right?
Fine.
I'm in.
Yuki!
I hate that I saw
behind that door.
Do you, Yuno Gasai,
take this man, Yukiteru Amano,
to be your lawfully wedded
husband, for richer or poorer,
in sickness and in health,
as long as you both shall live?
I do.
Why?
Do you, Yukiteru Amano.
Why'd I look?
Take this woman, Yuno Gasai,
to be your lawfully wedded wife,
for richer or poorer, in
sickness and in health.
I would have.
As long as you both shall live?
Maybe.
What if I just forget
the whole thing?
I can do that, right?
Pretend it was a nightmare.
You've had quite a day.
You people really know
what you're doing here.
So it's your element after all.
I'm so jealous of your youth.
Sure wish my husband would take
a page from your enthusiasm.
He's so tied up with work
lately I hardly ever see him.
But, what are you going to do?
What does he, uh,
do for a living then?
Oh, he's a homicide detective.
Man. What kind of
insane coincidence
was it running into her?
Kay, wake up.
You're home now.
I need your key.
It's unlocked.
Yeah.
Power's out, looks like.
Makes it nice and atmospheric,
though, don't you agree?
What're you?!
What did you think
of the wedding place?
Prepare you for the future?
Why'd you send us?
Unless you!
Well, come on.
It's not like I could've scoured
this joint with
Yuno actually here.
I'm good, but not that good.
Did you go into that room?!
What's the matter, my love?
What's going on?
Very curious, this room.
Have you seen inside?
You had no right
to go poking around!
Oh, please.
If I stayed within
the bounds of propriety
what could I hope to uncover?
What in the hell?
What is this?
Bizarre place
for a bottomless pit.
I'm serious if I throw a rock
in I can't even hear it hit.
Yuno!
What the hell did you do with
the "stuff" that was in here?
I don't follow.
The damn things that
were piled in here
the last time I was over!
You were?
Wait, you...
You don't remember?
Why are we hanging around
out here being eaten alive
by mosquitoes when
I could be playing hostess
for you fine gentlemen
in the parlor, huh?
Come on.
I don't want the first
time you come over
to leave a bad taste
in your mouth.
I don't understand.
There's a clinical term.
It's referred to as
cognitive dissonance.
And that means what, exactly?
Well, In this case it means her
mind's rewritten her memories
to maintain some
semblance of control.
She's that unstable.
Listen to me.
You probably think I'm a
bastard for pulling this stunt.
But I thought it would
help her confront the truth.
Obviously.
I was wrong.
Do you understand?
You're a stabilizing
influence on her.
She needs you.
But I...
Yuno.
Alright, folks.
Pay close attention.
The victim is our
dog murder suspect.
We found him with
a bullet in the head.
Coroner says he
was killed two nights ago.
Lucky for us, we have
a couple of leads.
They're likely perps, actually.
Yukiteru Amano, and Yuno Gasai,
both of them the ripe
old age of fourteen.
I want these little
punks brought in.
and I want them
within twenty four hours!
♪ closing song ♪
Maybe I misspoke;
maybe the whole
girly thing isn't so
gut-wrenching after all.
Ho-ho!
Why don't we bring it out
of you just a little bit more?
Huh?
What the hell are you doing?!
Take a look.
Ugh! What would ever possess
you to give me a topknot?!
Calm down if you don't like
it we can do something else.
Not really the issue, is it?
At least give me
something more up-to-date!
Okay.
What is wrong with you?!
Ugh...
You're so difficult.
How about the Kurusu do?
Or, we could go trendy afro.
Masculine topknot?
Oh god.
This is starting to bore
me, just so you know.
Clean slate!
I'll kill you.
You think I don't know
you're doing this on purpose?!
Come back here you little...
As if! You're totally
going to slug me!
A new do.