I'm sorry, love.
It's alright.
Let's go.
Are you not listening to me?
Whoever the hell that girl is,
she most certainly
isn't who you think!
Shut up!
I don't give a damn.
I should've been more persuasive
when making my case
for him to drop her.
Eleventh is John Balks,
aka the mayor of this
podunk little backwater.
Watch your ass, Eleventh.
I'm coming.
We'll be splitting up
into nine teams.
Once a perimeter
has been established,
each team is to hold...
You can't sit on the fence.
It's Time to settle on
which side looks greener.
Don't whine about it.
This is how choices get made.
The rest of you can suck it.
Godhood becomes me.
Huh...
What's this crap?
Defense schematics?
I'll be damned.
This pays off the
remainder of my debt.
Shop's closed from now on.
♪ opening song ♪
Oily bastard.
Why this place?
The hell is all this?
Somewhat imposing, yes?
A little.
We call it Holon Three;
the third largest
supercomputer in the country.
Exquisitely helpful.
Why do I shudder to
hear you use that word?
Perhaps a pang of misgiving as
to my intentions for your diary?
Every man, woman and
child in Sakurami has been
allotted a mobile
account that routes
through this
magnificent pylon.
For what possible reason?
Is it not obvious?
When I connect the Propagation
Diary to Holon Three,
every citizen will
become a Diary Holder!
Empires traffic in powers
beyond the ken of
their vassal lands!
Macedonia, Rome, Germany!
Sakurami will stand beside
them in the annals of history!
A city of prophets to
which all others shall bend!
My ass!
You're a lunatic!
Que sera sera, dear.
Oh crap!
Drop this?
HQ.
Team Three reporting.
There's been an explosion!
The terrorist has reared her
head right on schedule.
Deal with her
accordingly, would you.
Sir.
This is some bullshit!
How was he not surprised?
Screw it.
East lab it is.
Team Six.
We'll try to grab her en route.
What?!
Someone tell Team Five
to cover the East lab, STAT!
What the Hell?
Is this a Clairvoyant
Diary type of deal?
He's culling intel
from his toadies?
No... They haven't
even seen me yet.
She'll make a b-line for
the men's dormitory.
Yes, sir.
I see all, Ninth.
There is no escape.
Team Six checking in.
I'm sorry.
No sign of her.
Do you think she's on to us?
Don't worry about it.
Keep patrolling.
Team Nine, head for
the women's dorm;
she's on her way there next.
If you can,
cut her off at the pass.
What is this?
Nishijima to Headquarters.
I just saw a person
skulking toward the quad.
It was definitely
no one I recognize.
Teams Five and Six
go check it out.
What are you trying to pull?
Thought we were
done with each other.
Well...
Let's just say I got tired
of sitting on the fence.
And here's the part where you
tell me what changed your mind.
Okay...
You did.
Shut the hell up!
I'm being proposed to?!
Oh god.
Oh god!
Nobody gave you permission
to put that on me!
Would you please
stop freaking out?
Excuse me for wanting more for
myself than being a
frigging baby factory!
I think you'd make
a wonderful mom.
You'd be wise to
surrender your diary.
Why continue to let blood
heap senselessly on blood?
I am asking you for your help.
And I believe you.
Too hot in here?
I don't wear this
to be whimsical.
You asked.
I'm giving it to you.
Don't look a gift
horse in the mouth.
Will you slow down, please?
At least give me
some kind of answer!
This isn't the
time or the place!
Our illustrious mayor's battier
than a chimp on speed!
It'd be easier to deal with him
if you had and
extra pair of hands.
Let go or you'll need them!
What's with you?
I'm not the sort of
gal who's waiting
for her knight in
shining armor, okay?
Stop acting like I'm
sentencing you to life!
I'd rather stamp out
license plates, actually.
I need you.
A-ha!
Pervert!
Will you give me a break here;
I'm bearing my damn soul!
Let's you and me make
a little agreement.
Help me and I'll consider
it without retching.
Alright.
Good a start as any,
under the circumstances.
Why is this
getting under my skin?
This guy's a joke.
I'm a loner.
A rebel.
I blow shit up.
We've got a visual!
This is Team Six we have them!
Case in point.
How much longer till the
Propagation Diary is
fully connected?
Just a matter of moments.
She's through here!
Yes she is.
That is so cheating!
Misguided fool.
A shambling, one-trick
pony with a diary
every bit as absurd as
your confidence.
The Watcher renders all
notion of escape obsolete.
This is the
Electronics Lab team.
The Assailant has been captured.
This is it.
One big, happy family, sir.
Sorry guys afraid you're
in for a hollow victory.
Follow my lead to hell.
Minene!
Are you out of your mind?
You...
Don't even start!
What the hell are you doing?!
Not the best
career move, really.
Looks like I can
say goodbye to the
moral high ground for a
little while, too, huh?
After all that?
It couldn't have been this easy,
he knew every angle.
No way, Mr. By the Book
surprised him.
Except he doesn't have a diary.
Hold on.
I see you're not dry-heaving.
Uh...
Slow down!
Come on, am
I really all that bad?
Look, it's complicated.
I...
um...
Oh god.
We got a code red, people.
A patient's threatening suicide.
Requesting backup.
Please... Come off the
ledge and let's talk about this.
You don't get it!
I die tomorrow!
Hey these are
tomorrow's stock prices?
We're gonna have sukiyaki
tonight, aren't we mom?
That's right.
Are you reading mom's mind?
Okay that's bizarre.
When did I post
on my blog today?
Crap!
What in the hell is going on?!
A testament to the power of
redundancy, don't you think?
The portion of Holon
Three damaged in their
ill-advised attack was
entirely peripheral.
The dawn of our glory
shall not be denied!
That's check and mate, boss.
Tough luck.
Ninth doesn't have a snowball's
chance in hell as long
as the nature of Eleventh's
diary stays on the DL.
Ah...
The silent treatment.
That's alright.
Things are going well.
Murmur.
That's my name.
I feel I should
rest for a spell.
Good idea; you do that.
She is up to something,
any fool could see it.
Should I counter her move before
what power I have left
deteriorates further?
Clearly, I am in need of aid.
I hate this.
They might be coming at
us with tanks for all I know.
Who the hell are
you trying to call?
I think Akise will
know what to do.
The twink?
Booya!
Totally called it!
Wait, you're Akise's...
What up?
Good to see you
again, detective.
Cool.
He beat us here.
Hope you haven't
been waiting long.
I'm not getting
why you're even...
Fuck me.
So who's got what diary?
Feast your eyes on the badass
Neo Kousaka King Diary.
A block busting
play-by-play of me and
my posse in all our
unadulterated epic-ness!
Groan.
This is the friendship diary.
As you can guess it
keeps track of what I'm
doing with the peeps.
And I call this my
Lovely Hinata Diary.
It's like a digital scrapbook
of Hinata's life so far.
Hold on.
Excuse me?
Kind of stalkerish.
We haven't talked about this?
No!
No... don't read it!
"The nurse gave
us physicals today.
Hinata's boobs are,
like, humongous.
Hooray for."
Hooray for boobies!
Hooray for Hinata!
What is wrong with you!
Stop acting like a B!
You had no right to look
at it anyway--give it back!
Who are you people and
why the hell are you here?
Akise told me to show
up and help you guys out.
Said you'd be, like,
completely cut off, or whatever.
My diary basically told
me the same thing.
Mine didn't;
I was just tagging along.
Imagine that.
Checks out, I guess.
Where is Akise?
I asked him to come but he said
he was busy with something.
What're these Holon
things all about?
Give it.
Hey! It's my ass
if you break it!
Of course!
There's more than one!
Balks survived the explosion?
Looks like we're
gonna need some serious
computer geekage
in our corner on this one.
Or we take another crack at it.
According to this, the two
main units are housed on
the penthouse floor of
the Quad Tower downtown.
It's not gonna be a
straightforward
cord yank, though.
The units have to be put out of
commission simultaneously.
Meaning we're gonna
have to assemble a team.
And, we're here.
So, you know.
Aw, seriously.
Screw that, I'm putting
my foot down on this one!
This crazy bitch
is responsible for
blowing up half my damn school!
What I'm about to do is
gonna make your school
look small time.
You're psychotic!
I'll take both Quad Tower
units on my own.
You can go home.
Damn right we can!
I'm better off without you.
Get outta here, fur balls.
Is there some special reason
you chased those kids away?
No not really.
Unless you think
it's special of me not
to wanna see them get killed.
Same goes for you, incidentally.
Why are you still here?
Got a bun in the oven, huh?
Don't be a dick.
Get out of here.
I told you, I've done
my time on the fence.
I guess we better get a move on.
About damn time.
Son of a bitch, you're in.
Hey...
Good luck saving the city
without its resident badass!
You're gonna need me up there.
I couldn't sleep
last night thinking
about you two doing
this on your own.
I just didn't have
anything better to do.
Fantastic.
Don't worry about it,
sugar, we got this.
When I said resident badass,
I mean one with a weapon.
Let our enemies
try to pull a fast one
on us with this mamma
jamma in the mix!
I see you up there, douche bags!
Idiot.
I know, right?
Hey, this is brilliant!
Wait, that's it!
Bastard knew every
move I was gonna
make before I so
much as wriggled a toe.
But somehow Nishijima
found his blind spot.
What's he got that I don't?
Please don't be
what I think it is.
Deus!
Welcome, Ninth.
I've brought you here to
extend something of a proposal.
Excuse my caution
but we needed privacy.
From Murmur.
Sure, whatever.
I have a question.
Well?
Are you going to pose it or not?
What was that?
Am I losing it?
They've arrived.
What shall we do, sir?
They've split into two groups.
One's in the South Tower,
the other's in the North.
Both riding the
elevators to twenty.
Go time, people.
Operation Starling's
in full swing.
Intercept them when they get
off the elevators, please.
Kill them all as cleanly
as you possibly can.
Yes, sir.
We're in position
at the South Tower.
Copy that.
North Tower's covered.
Wait, what?
We've got nothing!
I beg your pardon?
Got you, you slippery bastard!
Keep tabs on us now!
This is not possible.
Sucks that all you can do
is spy on other diary users.
The Watcher's power is
unique, to say the least.
Do not think that because I
devised this game the concept
for it sprang from my
mind free of outside suggestion.
Eleventh had a formative
hand in the process.
Seriously?!
The diaries I must
credit to his imagination.
He persuaded me to
share a touch of my divinity
with mankind so as
to hasten its evolution.
It was vital that
each diary reflect the
personality of its user,
lest the game grow tiresome.
Together we conceived a variety
of applicable archetypes.
The Radar, for example,
whose predictions
function by proximity.
The Searcher, which foretells
the actions of a given target.
The Organizer, whose focus
is on that of a specified group.
The Supplier, bestowing the gift
of prophecy upon
third party users.
And finally, The Watcher--
Eleventh's invention a diary
capable of integrating
the predictions
of all other diaries in play.
So he's essentially
been monitoring the
rest of us from the word go.
Correct.
He created this game for
humanitarian purposes.
So he assured me.
Humanitarian?!
Are you fucking blind?!
I'll show you humanitarian!
Do your thing.
Already got
the entry
three-fourths
altered, sweetheart.
Edit our diaries,
screw with his.
Hey, I'm a veteran blogger:
bullshit entries
are my specialty.
Less talky, more typy.
We can't seem to pinpoint them.
Neither team can
find any trace of them
in the areas that
were specified.
A diversion.
Starlings tend to
travel in huge flocks,
making an ungodly racket.
Information overload
make it hard for the
enemy to separate
signal from static.
Have they puzzled out that
I can monitor their diaries?
So be it.
We might actually
stand a chance.
If we're lucky.
Please tell me when this
is all over with you'll trade
in the whole hard ass
shtick for a wedding ring.
Stop with that!
We've got more important
things to worry about.
No!
Minene!
You okay?!
Damn it, get the
hell away from me!
Oh fuck.
Nishijima!
Of course false
information plays havoc
on The Watcher's effectiveness.
Elementary.
And yet my diary, which
keeps meticulous track
of the orders you're to
give me remains unaffected.
The threat has passed.
Don't really feel like
a badass right now.
If you had quit screwing around
we wouldn't be in this mess!
Uh-uh.
Stay with me, man.
I'll be fine.
Just get out of
here while you...
Don't even finish that thought!
Damn it, listen.
There no, point
worrying about me now.
I love you!
You stupid son of a bitch!
Little too close for comfort,
don't you think?
First.
Why.
We've been hanging back so
you guys could lead the way.
We were your decoys?
We wouldn't have
had a prayer without ya!
Get those hands dirty, my love.
Yep! How much do
I want you right now?
What the hell you
think you're trying to pull?
Stick around,
you might learn something.
Hi there, Pookie.
Rock n' roll.
What are they doing here?
They're civilians.
That makes them useful.
Think about it for a minute.
Balks is the mayor.
He's a man of the people.
♪ closing song ♪
This ride is gonna be awesome!
I can't wait to give it a whirl!
I wouldn't get
my heart set on it.
What, you think I'm too
short to get on, is that it?
Well, they do have a sign.
I got a little
something-something' for that.
Candy?
Yeah, right!
More like chewable
growth supplements
that can futz with my age.
"I can ride the rides
today, do-dah, do-dah!
Roller-coasters 'til we spray!
Were you that
upset that you couldn't
go on these rides
last time around?
Hey, it ain't no crime to be
fun-sized, so spare me the pity!
Somebody's short-tempered.
Incoming!
Watch as Gigantic
Murmur levels the city!
Run for your lives, puny humans!
Oh I am so riding that!
I'm gonna ride it until
my butt goes numb!
Hey, lady?
Speak, primate.
The train well, it's meant
for grade-school kids,
so you're outta luck.
Are you serious?
But I love the little train!
Son of a--!