I won't deny it.
I am in fact, the serial killer.
It's quite simple, my dear,
I'm compelled to
eliminate suspected
Diary Users before they
turn the tables on me.
I spare no thought
for the lives I've taken.
I do, however, regret
allowing my obsession
to take me from you
and your mother.
Dad, I...
My entire purpose
for assuming the
Throne of Time was the
vain hope of restitution.
For us.
There's no reason
we can't make it work!
Look, I'm here for you, okay?
Whatever it takes, I'm all in!
The shadows lengthen
for me, I fear.
That weirdo?
His unrelenting
knack for spying on me
would suggest he has a Diary.
He's nothing...
You can't be serious.
Much as I long for us to start
anew, the boy is an obstacle.
What if I could do
something about that?
Give me what I want,
and we're cool.
And don't try to
play innocent, freak.
I'm on to you.
Are you telling me
Akise is a Diary User?
Duh.
No...
You know what?
I staged my own grisly
death so the pack of us
could come out of this
thing a little bit closer.
Fact is, his diary's
got a blind spot
when it comes to
the dearly departed.
So, this was all just a ploy
to get the drop on Akise?
Sorry, pumpkin you
were the perfect bait.
He's been on to you for weeks.
Come on, you can't blame a girl
for stacking up her advantages.
Don't be like that.
You barely know me.
Bad enough you had to chuck
a monkey wrench into my plan.
You used me.
Fine...
You want it, you can have it.
But please...
...just indulge me for a second.
Guess which hand.
♪ opening song ♪
So, I have my diary
and you have Amano's.
Which is good.
Level playing field.
I like that.
I propose we wager our
respective holdings in a
friendly little gamble,
if you're feeling lucky that is.
As if luck has
anything to do with it
when I can tell
the frigging future.
Really didn't think that one
through too carefully,
did you, Sherlock?
You think it'll be
simple as all that?
You're hardly the
only one here for
whom the future
makes itself known.
Why is this nutcase so damn
cocky all of a sudden?
Hinata...
Take him up on it.
He's just trying
to psych you out
cause he knows
Amano's diary is better.
Alright then.
Easy-peesy.
You're on!
Bring it!
First a warm-up toss.
Would you be so kind
as to do the honors?
According to this, the coin
will be in the right hand.
Cinch.
Okay, whatever
this is, I'm not a fan.
It'll be in her right hand.
Got it?
Kay! Which hand's
holding the glory?
Nice try, emo.
Next time, try not
to be so obvious
when giving your
pals the signal.
It's actually in my
left hand, so suck it.
Hate the game, not the player.
Oh, it's no big deal.
My diary's a bit
of stickler for details.
It's in your left.
Read them and weep.
Wait.
What?
How the hell did you?
I... you...
Is that really a Diary,
or is this guy just bluffing?
This... This is total b.s.!
Hold on...
There's more?
I don't like this one damn bit.
Okeydokey.
That'll do for a prelim,
I believe.
Let's play for keeps.
Eh?
I don't get it.
I mean, shouldn't Amano's
diary be able to predict
whatever is written
in Akise's diary?
Shut up!
Where oh where has
my little coin gone?
I have to get this!
It's in your right.
No points this round.
This guy's good!
Them's the breaks, chickadee.
Hand it over.
To hell with that!
How about I hand
over the kid instead?
You got a problem with that?
I agreed to your stupid game,
no reason it's got to
end after one round.
Amazing.
Dude, you're like a total boss!
We could play as
many rounds as she wants!
Bizarre...
His phone didn't make a noise
when the future got rewritten.
Something's not right.
Right.
Moving on, shall we?
First you have to
agree that if I win,
that makes this the
final round, yes?
No point dragging--
Sorry for all the fuss;
but I forgot to ask
you something important.
Who are you?
Which number?
What?!
Yuno, lay off him, he's
trying to get my diary back!
Sorry, my love.
You have to think
long term to survive.
Well, just look at
what we have here.
There's not a single
entry in this damn thing.
Excuse me?!
What's your game?
You're not a diary user.
He's been faking us
out the whole time?
Yeah, I may have lied a little.
Everyone was so adamant
about my having a diary,
I just kind of got caught up in
the spirit of things, you know?
It was infectious.
But... You won the
game twice in a row.
Sheer luck, my friend.
Good news for us, though:
it made Hinata doubt your
diary long enough to
turn the tide in our favor.
That's what this
was about, right?
Why'd you have to
go and spoil our lead?
You make it sound as though you
risked Yuki's life to
test a hypothesis.
Game over!
Sorry...
There's some life
in the game yet, I fancy.
Hinata wants me
dead cause I know
daddy dearest's
dirty little secret.
So I have what you might
call an honest incentive
to keep vying for Yuki's diary.
Now let's start playing
and be done with it.
Okay?
This is insane.
Think, man. You can't
get the better of someone
who can actually
tell the future!
If it's all the same to
you, sweet cheeks.
I'll decide myself.
You're crazy.
Even if he had a chance
in hell against my diary,
they're on to his trick now.
The whole thing's pointless.
Let's do it.
I'm curious to
see what you've got.
Goes without saying the stakes
are different now, though.
You win, you get Amano's diary.
I win, you become chew toys.
Hey, Hinata.
What?
Promise me something
before we do this again.
If we win,
promise me you'll, uh...
Well, I'd like us to still
be friends if that's okay.
Whatever.
And 'cause you're such a doofus,
I'll let you live regardless.
Are you out of
your mind, Hinata?!
The whole point was to keep
the skeletons in your
closet locked up!
Come on... You knew as well as
me this was a long shot.
Matter of fact,
you should leave.
Don't get me wrong:
I've been glad for the help.
It's just, I shouldn't have
gotten you into this mess.
Please forgive me.
Listen to him.
One doesn't expect to outwit
the Indiscriminate
Diary forever.
You're gambling
with my man's life.
I'm not okay with that.
And just so you know...
I don't trust you as far
as I could pummel you.
Well, just so you know, I'm
not in this to be an altruist.
Your man's a hottie.
--Hold on just a minute!
--Let's get this over with.
Ready when you are.
I'll make this fast.
Watch carefully!
Right hand or left?
This time I'm going to win.
The coin's in my right hand,
but he'll guess
wrong I know he will!
He has to!
Sweet pea...?
Mind if try
something real quick?
Okay.
Definitely...
...the right!
That son of a bitch!
How'd he know?!
Um... Sorry, Yuki...
I got it wrong.
Afraid we're
basically up a creek.
But... You... I... We...
What the hell are
we supposed to do now?!
Alrighty, then.
Now that Yuki's
sufficiently in the dark,
we can continue our little
back and forth.
I don't get it.
What's he stand to gain by
making him think they've lost?
Oh, crap!
Of course!
Wise to the ruse yet?
His diary reflects what
he thinks happened.
Yup.
An entry's only as reliable as
the perception it's based on.
You made him a false prophet.
Well, as long as
we're pointing fingers,
I'd like to remind everyone
that your little hoax out there
in the woods twisted his
perception of the future first.
So, I'm hardly the only
person in this room to
make him call into question
his phone's knack for accuracy.
You clever bastard.
I actually planned
on telling him I'd
lost this round whether
I guessed wrong or not.
Either way,
the point was to inhibit his
ability to truly
know what came next.
Okay, you lost me
with that last part.
How would that
have helped you win?
There was no guarantee I'd win.
But, hey, fifty-fifty
odds are pretty good,
all things considered.
I took a gamble and it paid off.
Plain and simple.
You lose, my dear. Sorry.
Mao?
No...
You get away from her!!!
You people...
It's not enough my dad's
on the chopping block.
Now you've got to take away
my only friend in
the entire world?!
I... I'm sorry.
Come on.
Now's not the time to let her
play on your sympathies.
Oh Mao...
Don't worry.
It's gonna be okay.
I stopped the bleeding before
you lost too much blood.
Alpha One!
Resume the hunt!
Rip them all to shreds!
All pack leaders follow Alpha
One's example and show no mercy!
I want every dog on their ass!
Oh crap.
Do you hear that?
We're all going to get eaten!
Why did this have to happen?
This isn't what I wanted.
This isn't my future!
Transfer ownership?
Yeah, Tenth tried
to reassign his diary,
but Deus put the kibosh on it.
Said the game would
be chaos if players could
bow out whenever they
felt the net closing in.
Are you sure that was Tenth's
only reason for asking?
He strikes me as the type
of man who loses all
sense of propriety when his
back's against the wall.
I suspect he's not
above entangling
innocent people in
his bid for survival.
He's a psychopath.
What are you doing?
You go on without me.
There's no way in hell
we're gonna outrun a
pack of dogs and you know it.
I'm going to stay behind.
See if I can't get
Hinata to call them off.
Darling, no.
Best be on your way.
Instead of taking the whole
problem on by yourself,
though, how 'bout the three
of us distract the pack?
We'll lead the hellhounds on a
wild goose chase
though the park;
you reach Hinata without
teeth marks on your ass.
Nuh-uh!
You don't just volunteer
me for that b.s.!
I'm sorry you have
something better to do?
Are you at least with me, Yuno?
It is a good plan.
Then let's make it happen.
Huh? What? Hey!
What are you doing?
Following me wasn't
part of the deal!
You've got to think long term.
We can use them as
our opportunity to get out
of this without being eaten
alive by those dogs!
You know...
If we use them as decoys,
we stand a pretty
good chance of
getting out of here.
We're not using them!
If I can get to Hinata,
we'll all be out of harm's way!
What makes you think you
can talk sense into her, huh?
You only just met her today!
And she played you!
I know, it's just...
Don't take this the wrong way,
but this is a bone-headed
idea from start to finish!
I know what this is about:
you're trying to make
friends and it's not worth it!
I'm not going to do it!
I'm not going to go back
to being the outsider!
Idiot!
You're too sentimental!
Whatever you're about to do,
please give it a second thought!
How many times
do I have to tell you,
sweetheart the only
friend you need is me.
You just want me to be alone.
You can't stand the thought of
anyone else being in my life.
Why?
Yeah, great idea: nothing to it!
And they've got backup.
Awesome.
Hey, if we get out of
this with our lives we'll
have Yuki to thank for it...
'less of course
he drops the ball.
Great...
They've lost track of
Amano and the psycho.
I didn't mean for things
to turn out this way, Mao.
I'm sorry.
But I'm not ready
to go home Mommy!
There's a ton of
rides we haven't
gone on and it's still daylight!
Don't throw a fit, dear.
This place is close
enough that we can
come back whenever
you'd like to, alright?
Try to think of your
father once in a while?
I've seen quite enough.
Let's go home.
Promise me that
if you win, you'll...
Well, that the two of
us can still be friends.
There's no point trying
to be my friend, Yuki.
Trust me.
Oh god.
Please someone come
and pull me out of this!
You're really gonna
go through with it?
I still say the best
course of action is to
leave them all to
rot and run like hell.
Not happening.
Oh, pookie.
Don't even!
Darling?
There's no good
reason I can't do this!
When the smoke clears,
we'll all be friends!
Oh shit.
Alpha One, come!
Calling Alpha Two and Three.
Call them off or
I slit your throat.
Alpha One stand down...
I Repeat, stand down!
Now hand over the diary.
No, please!
You wanna die, bitch?!
Let go of me!
Yuno, stop!
She's the enemy.
All we need is the diary; you
don't have to take it this far.
She tried to kill you!
At the very least she deserves
a knife to the jugular!
She surrendered;
stop adding insult to injury!
Come on...
You and I both know what
this is about, don't we?
You want me alone.
Course I do...
Think about it: where
would I be if you got to
know this girl and
fell in love with her?
Life, just wouldn't
be worth living if I
can't be the center
of your whole world.
Whore's got to go.
You hear me?
Same applies to anyone who
tries to shoulder in on my Yuki!
All of you have
been trying to drive a
wedge between us
from the very beginning!
Now I get it.
You understand,
don't you, my love?
I'm all the friend
you'll ever need.
Right?
Enough!
You have never been my friend.
Don't say that!
Damn it let me finish!
You're not my friend, Yuno.
I'm sorry.
Hinata.
Akise.
Kousaka.
Yeah, that's my name.
I would like to introduce you
all to someone very special.
This is Yuno Gasai.
My, uh, girlfriend.
Yuki.
You just called me your
girlfriend didn't you?
Don't spoil the moment;
I'm trying to be a
gentleman here and
introduce you to the gang.
I've waited long
enough as it is.
He's brilliant.
Wow, they already act
like a married couple.
You've got more guts in you
than I would have thought emo.
Nothing like taking
one for the team, huh?
Listen, Yuno...
July 28th.
That's when we live
happily ever after, right?
Try not to over-think it.
Look at them.
All I ask is that you accept
these people as my friends.
You can start by
apologizing to Mao.
Come on, you don't
want to be one of
those girlfriends
everybody hates, do you?
Read me?
Yeah?
I do.
Now what?
What the hell have
I gotten myself into?
I don't understand;
why'd you do it?
I'd have killed you
given the opportunity.
It wasn't your fault.
It was circumstance.
That's all.
I dropped the ball, dad.
Guess you've been right
about me from day one.
The boy's right, my dear.
It wasn't your fault.
I set you on the wrong trail.
Yeah, but...
It's over, Hinata.
Don't talk like that!
Please!i
There's still a chance you can
win that throne and
reboot the family!
And why would I want to do that?
Don't you know a bald-faced
lie when you hear one, girl?
I swear, an inbred beagle
has more sense that you!
Dad.
Don't.
The most you'll ever
get out of dear old dad
is a negative example.
But that's...
I've got an ambulance
on the way, so...
Us, one,
Collateral Damage, zero.
Because my Yuki
followed his instincts.
No question.
I am a little surprised that you
came out of this
unscathed, though.
Anyone else's instincts
probably would've led them
to dispose of the loose cannon
rather than try to appease it.
Beware...
Those who seem kindest
are often the most
insidiously cruel.
Few people, if any,
can be trusted to the end.
Don't you agree?
Fourth?
[gunshot]
♪ closing song ♪
So this is where Karyudo
Tsukishima calls home.
They say his dogs
eat like kings,
and Murmur wants in
on that gravy train!
And now, my dogs shall
feast like the princes they are!
Your dinner awaits!
But first!
Roll-call!
Woof!
Bark-bark!
Pop quiz.
What's the top
of a house called?
Roof!
The roof!
Question number two.
If something
is difficult, it is...!
Ruff!
That would be Ruff!
Two down!
Question three!
What is this called?!
Bowl!
A bowl!
We have an
interloper in our midst!
So, my boss Deus
has decided that you're
gonna be one of his
twelve diary keepers.
Pretty cool, huh?
You're still wearing that?