♪ opening song ♪
I really need to start using my
diary for more practical things.
If I had known she
was going to be late,
I wouldn't have gotten
here at four on the dot.
Hey! Hey!
There he is!
Sorry, champ.
You wait long?
Yep.
I swear you'd think
I'd been gone a year
as much as you've grown.
Yeah, well it's only been
a month so whatever.
Here he goes with the attitude.
This is not going
to be a good day.
This is my mom.
She's a big shot game
developer, or whatever.
She travels a lot for work
which, honestly, I'm fine with.
Then I guess it'll
be my default.
Steak hamburguesa.
So why did the
brass let you off?
Um.
Something.
Kind of came up.
I'll explain it to you later.
Change of subject.
Some lucky cheerleader
make my son a man yet?
Ugh! What is wrong with you?!
C'mon, you can tell me.
Most moms freak out
about that kind of thing.
Well, sure.
'Cause they're idiots.
Sorry.
Crazy stalker's
the best I got for you.
Uh, Yuki.
Was the window
broken before you left, or?
So...
That's a no.
Oh no.
Uh, yeah! It was me.
I was rough-housing,
or whatever would cause that.
Why don't you get dinner
started and I'll go wash up!
Yuki!
Of all the days for
her to pull this!
Welcome back home, my love.
We're not playing house!
What the hell are you
even doing here?!
It's okay,
I'm just trying to make a
good impression on your mom.
We want her to like me, right?
Scrub, scrub, Scrub, scrub.
Oh, hello.
Wow, that smells amazing.
Get out of here
before she sees you!
I want to meet her.
Damn it.
Uh.
C'mon.
Since when do you cook?
Son of a!
The jig is up if
you don't think fast!
Last I checked you
couldn't even boil water.
This is the part where
you tell me I look pretty.
Hey, Julia Child.
I'm talking to you.
Crap!
What am I gonna do?!
Are you in your room?
What's that all about?
Oh, just...
Stretching.
You know.
So, yeah, dinner's on me, huh?
You can't leave the stove on
while you're not here, doofus!
Sorry.
I'm still new to
the whole concept.
Not good, It isn't
like Yuno was just
in the neighborhood and
decided to drop by.
She's got it in her head
to make friends with mom.
Oh wow.
Cleaning too, huh?
Yes?
Who are you and what
have you done with my Yuki?
Bet you're surprised.
Oh wow, she sounds
like a total angel.
I've got to meet her!
Let me out.
Hey.
Was that...
Was that a girl's
voice I just heard?
Probably just
the house settling.
Let me outta here.
Ah!
You're telling me
you don't hear that?
Seriously, do you lift weights
in your spare time
or something?!
Knock it off!
Son of mine.
What's up?
Care to tell me why you're
arguing with a closet?
What?
Nobody's arguing.
Normally this is called leaning.
You must think
I was born yesterday.
Do you really think I
can't see you straining.
My poor child.
Trying so valiantly
to hide his little girlfriend.
That's my cue!
Time to push out
and say "Hi, Mom!"
Move it, kid.
This is pointless.
Yuki.
--Open the door!
She's out of bounds!
You did not just do that!
Oh, you're in for it now!
Best let the woman
cool her jets a bit.
Why are you looking at those?!
Or, an even better
question maybe...
Why are they here?
So, Yuno Gasai.
Mercy, how incredibly
adorable are you?!
Why anyone would want
to keep a girl like this a
secret from their
mother is beyond me.
Oh, just look at her face.
This may be the
worst day of my life.
Uh, excuse me, ma'am, but,
I steamed some vegetables
if you'd like to try a bite.
Interesting.
Good luck with that, Yuno.
Mom's a confirmed foodie.
There's not a pickier
palate in the world
when it comes to culinary stuff.
Ah! Well done,
my dear!
You're pulling my leg, right?
That's some serious
talent you've got.
Very impressive.
You've practically got a little
showcase going on here.
I know Home Ec prodigies
when I see them.
Thank you!
This family could
use a gal like you.
You think?!
Oh, I'd love to get you
in a fancy wedding dress.
Or, something more
traditional, maybe.
Are we talking a
Shinto ceremony?
Modernism's got
it's good points too.
Why do I get the feeling the
rest of my life hangs
in the balance?
Where do the years go?
Kids grow up so fast,
one minute you're
buying them cereal,
the next cruise vouchers.
There's hardly time to
get a handle on them
before they've plunged
right into adulthood.
Son of mine.
Oh god!
Birds and Bees time.
Seal the deal!
Oh wow.
Don't think I would pimp
my boy out to anyone.
You seem like a nice girl.
Really, ma'am,
that's very sweet.
I'm not late to the party, am I?
Have you two already done it?
I hate my life.
Well...
Damn.
They definitely yanked
it out like a pro.
You going to start
referring patients to him?
I know that tone.
Here you go.
Right color and everything.
Just understand...
you're probably gonna look a
little wall-eyed before you
get the hang of it.
So, who was this beast
who got the best of you?
Shut up.
Unless you got a death wish you
need to change the subject.
So testy.
Hope you don't
lose the other eye.
Shove it, pops.
When'd you go
kid clinic, by the way?
Oh, that.
Sad story, actually.
You're looking at
the real casualties
of the Omekata Cult massacre.
Most of them probably
saw their folks die.
They were in the shrine?
Child Welfare wants me to
evaluate them for
foster placement.
This is a legit doctor's office
two thirds of the time.
Official word on the cult's
death was mass suicide;
which, when you think about it,
isn't exactly a hard sell.
Particularly when the
truth puts their blood on
the hands of an axe-wielding
teenage cupie doll.
I imagine the powers
that be don't want these
kids clamoring for blood
when they get older.
You know what...?
Revenge sucks.
Believe me.
A kid's parents are
supposed to die first.
Oh, wait.
Get a load of him in this one.
Look at those cheeks!
Can you believe he
was ever this small?
Or ever not such a
royal pain in the kiester?
--He's not that bad.
--This is so humiliating.
Defending him now, are we?
Oh, Mom.
A-ha!
And this was his first
ever swimming lesson.
Aw!
Look at those cheeks!
What the hell pictures
are they looking at?
Somebody was P.O.'ed
about wetting the bed, huh?
What are you showing her?!
Mom!
Baby pictures.
You pervert!
I'm naked in all of these!
It's not like I let you go au
natural till you were twelve.
Can you two please just
look at something else?
If you want.
I can always show her my record
of when you got the chicken pox.
I hate my life.
If I'd known this was
going to be my day
when I woke up this morning.
And we're out.
Of course.
Here you go.
Sorry.
Get out!
The next melee
should be intriguing.
The whole shebang
is spicy if you ask me.
Every diary an extension
of the user's personality.
Less an extension
than a microcosm,
I think, but spicy all the same.
Uniqueness of character was my
chief criterion when
selecting participants.
Sure makes whoever's going to
succeed you anybody's guess.
You know, in theory the game
could go on
forever, couldn't it?
Might be a while
before they weed
each other out of the running.
I mean, rules are rules
and there're still nine
users in the mix.
Let's keep our fingers
crossed you can hold out.
Heh.
If they piddle around you'll
turn into Humpty Dumpty.
Doesn't surprise me.
He's had a keen eye for
other people's business
ever since he was a little boy.
Matter of fact, a month ago...
Oh, almost forgot.
My being here?
Work's given me paid
leave for the next three days.
Something the matter?
Well, uh...
Have you kids by any chance
been following the news
about that nutty suicide cult?
Yeah.
Well, turns out one of my
coworkers was a member.
They left behind a child and
the company wants me to
look after it while they
arrange things long-term.
How old a kid are
we talking about?
Two or three, I believe.
It's a little boy.
I offered to let him stay
here for a few days.
Best get ready for bed, Yuno,
it's too late to
let you walk home.
Uh, I don't think
that's a good idea!
Thank you.
You're so considerate.
But...
Oh crap!!!!
There's like five
other rooms she could
be crashing in besides mine!
Cut out the Puritan act.
All I ask is that you
try to keep it down.
Night-night.
Have fun storming the castle.
And keep that rascal
wrapped till you're married.
I hate life.
Screw that!
Hell no!
Sweetie, I'll leave
a fresh towel
for you on the vanity, okay?
You're the awesome-est mom ever.
Feel free to use my
body-wash, if you want.
Trust me, it's like
giving your skin a
dress rehearsal for the
post-party afterglow.
Okay.
One more thing, hon.
Yes ma'am?
Take good care of my boy, huh?
He's worth it.
Right.
Good night.
She's such a good mom.
The first time I have
a girl stay the night
and it's got to be a nut case.
Hey.
You going to put the
moves on me or not?
I'm going with or not.
Aw, loosen up.
Your mom said it's okay
if we mess around.
Look...
You're nice but I just
don't see you that, way.
Give it time.
Excuse me?
You're totally going to fall
in love with me soon.
Yeah?
What makes you so sure?
On the twenty-eighth
of July, we take things
to the next level and
become lovers.
See?
Uh.
You do know it's my prerogative
to change that future if I want.
That's fine.
And suddenly it's
fine just like that?
Would it kill you to make some
sense every once in a while?
Our happy ending
is what it is, Yuki.
I've got news for you,
if I don't like it, I'm...
Let's get something,
straight, kay?
It's my happy ending, too...
doesn't matter what you do.
Yuno.
On July 28th, it happens.
We join together in love
as a single soul.
Yuki... If, if it helps
consider it a challenge.
Going to sleep now!
The two of us.
Together.
I can't even imagine it.
Hey...
For you, sweetheart...
Anything.
I'm good at keeping an
eye on my sugar bear.
Okay, I'll admit she's,
like, painfully cute, but...
No!
Don't even start!
What's wrong with me!
My man has such a lovely,
understanding mother.
And here I thought I'd
have to get ugly with her.
Here we are kiddo!
Whatcha think?i
Wow!
Hey, be a sport and wait
for me on the porch, will ya?
I'm gonna pull the car into
its secret hiding place.
Okey dokey!
I hope you kids
slept well last night.
Ha.
So, this is the fella
I was telling you about.
Hey, champ.
Can you tell big brother
and big sister your name?
I'm Houjou Reisuke!
What's your name big brother?
Hi there.
You can call me Yuki.
What do I call you, sis?
Oh, my name's Yuno.
Face hug!
Ho!
The kid's good.
Be sure to take off your
shoes before you come in.
Okey dokey!
Face hug.
Sloopy, sloopy,
sloopy, sloopy face hug.
Whoa.
Look at you.
Little dude's a drawing
fiend, aren't ya?
Awwww.
Yuno, look.
It's you.
I can tell from here.
Nice job.
It's a picture of
the woman I love!
Uh-oh, Yuki.
It sounds like you have a rival.
Afraid there's
no competition, Mrs. A.
Man.
This kid sure is chipper for
having just become an orphan.
I really hope...
Nah.
Not possible.
He couldn't know
Yuno was responsible.
Hey...
You're pretty good
at that aren't ya.
Aw.
Did you make that just for me?
Oh, honey you've
got to be careful!
Anybody get hurt?
I'm alright.
Oh crap!!
Yuno!
I'm good.
The cushion's another story.
Oops.
You're okay?
You're absolutely sure?!
Yeah, yeah they
didn't even graze me.
Close call.
Sweet pea.
Promise me you'll never
run with scissors again.
I promise.
Where you off to?
You good to go in there alone?
I'm a big boy!
Yuno Gasai.
This one's gonna be a bitch.
♪ closing song ♪
'kay, I'm ready!
Alright then, Yuno...
Shall we get started?
Target detects nothing amiss.
My disguise is genius!
The Amano family's
famed secret recipe for
miso soup is practically
in my hands!
Alright, I'm not going
to lie I'm a little nervous.
But, maybe if you
laid it out for me first.
It's not that hard when
you get right down to it.
The first order of
business is prepping our
ingredients with
the utmost care.
Item one: purified water.
What could be purer than water
from a glacier completely
unsullied by human hands
since the last Ice Age???
Item two:
unimpeachable soup stock.
No peaches on this beautiful
specimen, are there?
Ha-ha!
Item three: soy beans worth
moving heaven and earth for.
Dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig!
They always say you got
to keep the earth moving!
Sweetie, I think you've
outdone yourself!
Hey, anything worth doing
is worth doing right, isn't it?
My ex-husband could make
miso soup out of this stuff,
and he's a disaster
in the kitchen!
Damn it.
Give me a sec,
I sort of have to take this.
What is it?
I'm busy!
A disaster in
the kitchen, you say?
Sorry about that.
Ah.
Enthusiasm.
I like that about you.
--Here.
--Oh.
And a quick learner, too.
Let's see if it's fit
to be called Amano.
Stop looking at me like that;
it was an accident okay?
I'll make it up to her by
concocting at the very site
of my gaffe a batch of miso
soup worthy of the gods!
Item one: a little kick.
And some salt to
counteract that.
Some good-time
juice to fix that.
Which we offset by waving
our hands around frantically!
It's okay, it's okay.
What's that smell all about?
Is it coming from there?
Bizarre.
When'd mom get home?