Attention all units the
hospital has been
seized by three
apparent terrorists.
Assume the premises to be
heavily rigged with IED's.
That means seal it off people.
Swat team's just
off the truck, chief.
Tell them to get their
asses in there, STAT.
Uh, there's still quite
a few patients left inside.
I mean... your son.
Get the team in position.
Right away, sir.
Damn you.
♪ opening song ♪
Don't worry, hon.
You're too important to kill.
Where do my options
go if you're dead?
We're going to bait hubby
off the chess board, though.
Nice way of saying, kill him.
The ethics bothering you?
As long as my
Yuki gets out of this,
I don't give a damn
about the ethics.
I'm starting to think
I short-changed her,
calling her a stalker.
I mean, she's on her
own planet, yeah,
but hell the girl's committed.
And cute.
Alright.
Here's the deal.
I nominate myself to
spearhead negotiations.
Yuno, guard the hostages
and monitor your boy.
Yuki, take the perimeter.
The hell does that mean?!
What do I do?
You grow a pair.
Make a choice you
want left pocket or right?
Oh uh, the right.
Congrats.
You win a grenade.
Holy crap.
When you're ready to
use it, take out the pin,
throw, and take cover.
You'll have five seconds.
Aw what's wrong,
are you nervous?
Hey, sweetie?
You're low on ammo, right?
Take these with you.
Uh...
Thanks, but no thanks?
I'm a lousy shot anyway;
makes more sense for
you to hold onto them.
You're not going to
live with that attitude.
Yoo-hoo.
Any day now, rug rats.
Uh, Yuno?
Um...
If we make it out of here alive.
I, uh...
Kind of want to take
you somewhere special,
if that'd be cool.
Of course it is.
Sure. Okay.
Going now.
What's your angle in all this?
Huh...
You sound pissed for someone
who should've seen it coming.
Just make your demands.
You know the routine.
Give me swag, you get hostages.
First off, car...
Full tank of gas.
Then...
To get you outta
our hair permanently
I want you to kill yourself.
Not going to happen.
Hey! Think I'm kidding
around here?!
Your negotiating power
isn't what you think is.
The building's been
completely surrounded.
The only way out's a body bag.
Or you can swallow your
pride and surrender.
Did you miss the
part about the hostages?!
I have your family!
I'm perfectly aware who
you've got in there with you.
Thing is, you want to live,
you're going to let them go.
I'm the one calling
the shots here.
And the next one will
be through your skull.
I will kill your son,
you stupid bastard!
He's as good as dead whether
you're the one to do it or not.
His only hope is for me
to win this fucking game!
So it's about to
get real, sweetheart.
Swat team move in
and take them out!
Crazy son of a, bitch!
They're coming up, Yuki!
Get out of there now!
Are you listening to me?!
Move it!
Freeze, asshole!
Target reigned in!
Yuki?
Yuki, no!
Uryuu was supposed
to talk to him!
Holy shit the little bastard's
carrying a live grenade!
Keep him down.
Captain's on his way.
No, no, no!
Kurusu's going to kill us
all when he gets here!
What are you doing?!
She's got the hostages
in room 413.
Do whatever it takes
to get them out of there.
Sir, this is insane!
We don't have clearance
for these kinds of tactics.
Thank you, officer.
Your services will
no longer be needed.
Wait...
Seriously?
C'mon, think!
If I don't get out
of here, I'm dead!
I've got to break free!
He's out of his head!
It's over, Gasai!
Back off!
Oh yeah?!
Freeze!
Amano's my hostage!
Run away, Yuki!
You crazy!
You're mine!
Sea change, little girl.
Now back off!
--Don't you do it!
--Let him go!
Pull it, he dies!
I swear I'll kill us all!
You going to
bargain with his life?
Put down the damn grenade!
Back off of him right now.
Don't think I'm afraid
to blow us all to hell!
Five minutes.
Should hopefully do the trick.
We need something
in the way of distraction.
Even if it only buys the kiddos
a couple precious seconds.
Now comes the part where
I use my second best skill set.
--Oh, you're kidding me!
--You're kidding me!
Alright, listen.
We'll make a trade.
I'll let Yuki go,
if and only if,
you put that thing
down and back away.
Sure...
First move's all you.
Reasonable enough.
Step away slowly, Amano.
Well...
Go on, Yuno.
Don't worry.
I've got this.
What that hell does that mean?
Before you came into my life,
this world was pretty
much dead to me.
If we hadn't met, I wouldn't
have made it as long as I did.
We could be a family
if we got married?
We'll have to
wait till we're older.
Oh, Yuki.
This waiting is driving me nuts.
How much longer
till we're the right age?
C'mon, my love.
Grow up faster!
This is torture!
You were hope
personified for me.
You were life.
Even if we're not meant to be.
This is the least I can
do to pay you back.
I'm not afraid to die.
Really.
Because I'll still always
be a part of you.
You psychotic little...!
Let go of me!
This is where your future ends,
you son of a bitch!
No!
Don't do it!
You made a promise!
We had a date!
How, how do I keep
running into you?!
How do I keep running into you?
Uncalled for.
--Oh, you ass.
--This time, I've got you!
Was that what I...!
Way to go, Yuki.
Didn't think you had the grapes.
So that wasn't real?
It only incapacitates.
The idea is to buy
yourself some time.
As if I'd just hand a
deadly weapon to a kid.
So, uh...
Uh, I'm not an expert, but that
looked pretty damned real to me!
Well, that's probably
because it was real.
That's the bomb I set on four.
I'm so screwed if they're dead.
Hey!
Hold up!
Don't give me grief; you're
my ticket out of a Dead End.
Now shut up and pay attention.
Huh?
What's going on?
Yuno!
Oh, thank god.
Can you hear me?
No!
How are you still...?
Looks like Lady Luck
has a thing for me.
Sucks for you.
I'd give you the whole
"this hurts me more" spiel,
but it wouldn't
strictly speaking be fact.
Sorry it came to this.
Really, kid?
We both know
you don't have in you.
Even if you did...
How good's your aim?
Trust me,
you'll want to be sure.
I...
didn't mean...
You're not a killer.
Flip side, though I am.
Welcome back, sunshine.
I suggest that you behave.
You get wiggly on me,
I'm liable to slip and cut
your pretty little throat.
You won't win.
Ha! I believe the
woman has faith in you, kid.
I can't do this.
If I miss, I'll hit Yuno.
What am I supposed
to do, though?
Either way, she's a goner.
Give me something.
Damn it, no!
If I fire, Yuno's dead!
What do I do?
Problem?
Something in that diary
giving you second thoughts?
You're pale as death.
I can't drop the gun.
Without it, he wouldn't
waste a second killing us.
I hate this.
Shoot him, Yuki.
Go on, my love.
If it goes through
me, then so be it.
I still stand by what
I said about you and me.
Sure, you were just
calling me your girlfriend
to appease me
or whatever, but hey...
A girl in my position's
not about to look
a gift horse in the mouth.
I mean, come on.
You took it far enough
to do a mock wedding.
You need to shut
your mouth, girl.
You're satisfied for
him to lie to you?
You've got a lot to learn about
self respect, let alone love.
Stupid teenagers and
your B.S. make me sick!
Oh, man.
Yuno.
You've been carrying this thing
around with you the whole time?
Why not?
Because you ought
to have the sense
to want better for
yourself, damn it!
Why've you been
stalking me for a year if
you're willing to let
it end like this?!
We were going to be married!
I was just living in a dream.
Save...
Saving you is as
good as it'll get for me.
Shut up!
You deserve better than to be
treated like a sacrificial lamb!
I wasn't just calling you my
girlfriend to appease you!
You're going to be
my bride one day!
Maybe it's all just
been a dream to you.
But to me, it's reality!
Yuki.
If you want her
to die, go ahead.
If you care for her you'll
put down the damn gun!
I'm sorry, Kurusu.
Not an option.
Because I don't just
care for her... I love her.
How did you do that?
Goddammit, I'm not going to die!
I won't be taken out
by a punk like you!
I... I tried to warn you.
Please, just stop.
The throne of
space-time is mine!
I will become god!
I have to!
Put it down, chief.
Bang-on for timing, huh?
Kurusu.
Stay out of this.
I know you killed Karyuudo;
that you had the gall to try
and pin it on a couple of kids.
Uyruu and I had a good,
long talk on the way here.
What kind of cop takes the word
of a terrorist at face value?
A bad one.
Believe it or not, I've come
here to make a deal with you.
What'd you have in mind?
I'm offering to
call the uniforms off...
You got me.
Drop the weapon now.
You, you're under arrest.
Oh yeah?
How's it feel?
To be on the wrong
side of the law, I mean.
Your diary's useless
now, I'm afraid.
You know... since you're
no longer a real cop.
Makes sense, I guess.
How are my wife and son?
Good.
Swat team pulled them out
just before the bomb exploded.
They're shook up, but safe.
That's alright then.
Do me a favor, Ninth.
I hate to ask you to team
up with me again, but...
In return.
I'll deal myself out.
What are you doing?!
Watch over my son.
I can do that.
For what it's worth,
Yuki, I'm sorry.
Doesn't mean much coming
from a bastard like me, I know.
But you're going
to win this game.
I know it!
Detective Nishijima was put in
charge of his former
chief's cases, naturally.
As you might imagine,
the badges had a lot of
questions for Yuno and me.
Lucky for us the files
Kurusu used to cover his
butt went a long way
toward clearing our names.
It's hard to say
when he went rogue.
I like to think his better
side held out for a while.
Of course, the media made a
huge deal out of the whole mess.
Corrupt cops,
terrorists, all that.
But our names
were kept out of it.
And evidently, Ninth made
good on another escape.
Ah, crap!
I'm going to be late!
There was a silver
lining, though.
Turns out the cop
I shot survived
and is expected to
make a full recovery.
You going to keep me in
suspense the whole afternoon?
Maybe.
We're stopping by dad's place on
the way to pick up my telescope,
if that gives you a
clue what the plan is.
Think somewhere
with a good view.
I don't think there are words
for how happy I am.
Quality time with
my man, stargazing.
This'll be the romantic outing
to put all others to shame!
Wow...
No pressure or anything.
Oh, whatever!
It's going to be great!
Just live in the now!
That's what eternal
life is really all about.
You don't say?
Looks like somebody's
been practicing
their moves on the
pillow at night.
Aw, leave me alone.
We're sorry.
The party you're trying to
reach is currently unavailable.
Please try again later.
We're sorry.
Give me a break.
What's the matter, sweetie?
Dad's phone is out
of range, or something.
Thought he'd be home now.
Last one on board has
to massage the winner's feet!
What?
Yuno... Wait up!
Should I or shouldn't I?
Since the train's not here yet.
I'm going to go make a pit stop.
Back in a sec.
I'll get us something
to drink, too.
Kay.
Akise?
Who's that supposed to be?
Do I know this person?
Sorry about that.
Hey... You're going
to wind up losing this thing.
Thanks.
Did anybody try to call me?
You got some spam
but I got rid of it.
Kind of a large bag to
be taking on a day trip.
Yeah.
But hey.,,
When you surprise her, a girl's
gotta be prepared.
Were you expecting me to
take you on a tour of Europe?
No, silly.
I just thought I'd bring
a change of clothes,
and first aid stuff.
And maybe some unmentionables.
♪ closing song ♪
So to recap, you've been
chosen as a Diary Keeper;
if you have any
questions, now would
be the time to spit them out.
Large mocha,
extra whipped cream.
Thanks!
You're totally fabulous.
Thank you.
Well, enjoy.
Back when I was kid.
I wanted this model toy.
It was called a Gyan.
So, you like to be random.
Hey.
Listen.
A Friend told me I was an idiot.
Told me I ough
to go with a Zaku.
But I wouldn't be
talked out of that Gyan.
Well, my thing was always.
Just hear me out.
Alrighty.
I'm not rambling here;
this is how I became a cop.
See, I wanted the
Gyan so bad I stole it.
Sounds like the
opposite of being a cop.
The old man found out
about it from the shop keep
and beat the crap out of me.
So, he set you on
the straight and narrow.
My old man?
Like hell.
He's was a career criminal.
Specialized in
breaking and entering.
Should I be hunkering
down for a long one, or?
Mind you, he was unemployable,
so he didn't have much choice
if he wanted to survive.
Not that it helped
him last long.
Anyway, point is, I often
ask myself why no one
was there to beat
the crap out of him.
But you just said
that didn't help you.
Or are you saying you became
a cop so you could kick his ass?
Suppose that's one
way of looking at it.
Thanks for the diary.
Should come in very handy.
Always good
to know who you'll be
beating the ever
living crap out of.
Did he just make
off with my umbrella?