Where are you Yuki?
Akise!
Nishijima...
Hey.
What are you doing up here?
I haven't seen you in forever.
It's our stop.
No one ever said it has to be.
But this is where we were
going to look at the stars.
I've got a better spot in mind.
Don't you worry.
Uh, sure.
♪ opening song ♪
Fourth has become the next
keeper to trek thither into that
undiscovered country
from which no man returns.
I must admit to a
certain frisson of surprise.
My calculations had Fourth
in the game up until the end.
Rather odd, isn't it.
Not really!
What?
Mochi.
Aw, what the heck.
I might as well be
straight with ya, Boss.
Fourth shouldn't have known
that his kid was slowly
but surely kicking the bucket
until later in the game.
He would've sold out
Yuki and Yuno eventually,
but only after more
keepers bit the big one.
Trouble is, his presence
on the board was
stabilizing the game too much.
Boring!
So I maybe kind of sort
of gave things a nudge.
What are your motives, imp?
I want the same
thing you do, Boss.
A game that's fun to watch
and doesn't take
forever to play out.
We don't exactly have all the
time in the world, you know.
You're going to be
checking out any day now.
And we have to get
your successor ready to roll.
Hey, Deus.
What you say we spice
things up with a bet?
Yuki.
I'm kind of thirsty.
I'm going to go buy
a drink, if that's okay.
Oh, yeah.
The air seems
pretty clean up here.
I think we'll be able
to see the stars just fine.
One soda, coming up!
Huh?
I figured you
would be thirsty, too.
Thanks.
That stretch
I dedicate to Akise.
We owe him a big
thank-you for inviting us.
Ain't that the truth!
The view here is
simply breathtaking!
The scenery up here
is really beautiful, isn't it.
A hot spring?
And you're, inviting us?
Indeed.
I received these vouchers
from an acquaintance of mine.
Might as well celebrate
your recovery, right?
I'm going to make crab an
endangered species at dinner.
Is something the matter?
I could have of sworn I saw
a flash in the water just now.
It's just your imagination.
Yeah, must of been.
There's nothing in
here that could make a--
That was not my imagination!
Oh!
No, Hinata, please!
You have to put those away!
Look, something
keeps flashing down there
and I want to
know what it is?!
Hey, how come
your nose is bloody?
Uh...
Wait...
What you got there, huh?
Huh?
Oh, that?
A cell phone?
No shit, Sherlock!
Now tell me why you
dragged the damn thing
into the bath with us!
I was expecting
an important call?!
Too bad!
Now give me that phone!
No, I need it!
Dammit, Mao!
Stop squirming!
Stop grabbing at me you pervert!
Me?! You just
double-high-fived my boobs!
A zip-line?
That's right.
They say you can see
for miles around as you go.
Aw, that sounds
like a yawn-fest.
But as long as
we're here anyway,
I guess we should
give it a whirl.
Guess who just ganked,
like, all the crab!
Man... This is why
we can't take you anywhere.
I don't mean to be rude, but
why is he on this trip, again?
Well... I had an extra voucher
so I figured what the heck.
I guess.
So what's boy detective
jotting down over there, huh?
That your actual diary?
More or less.
Whatever!
I bet you it's not as
cool as this baby!
Behold the Kousaka King Diary,
a chronicle of my
rock-tacular triumphs!
That's the worst
diary in all of history.
Some grade-school
kid write those for ya?
Grade-school kids
don't rock this hard!
Why do you call yourself a
commoner in your own diary?
Is this some online journal?
I'm assuming it's
programmed so that
your ranking improves
as you post.
Guys, enough with
the damn diaries already.
You're going to turn into
Yuki if you don't watch out.
Speaking of, I wonder
what he's up to right now?
Dude probably got
his ticket punched.
Whoa.
What's your problem?
I'm going to grab more
crab... I'll be right back.
Uh, okay then.
What in the hell
are you screaming for?!
Hinata just mentioned Yuki!
I don't understand why
she'd be thinking about
him out of the blue like that!
The chief's casebook.
"The serial killer was Hiyama
Takao, keeper number three.
Uryuu Minene, a.k.a.
Ninth, was the school bomber.
Sixth and Twelfth,Tsubaki
Kasugano and Yomotsu Hirasaka,
were behind the cult massacre."
"Fifth, Houjou Reisuke, was
the assailant at Yuki's house.
The dog murders
were Karyuudo Tsukishima.
He's Tenth."
"The hospital bomber was
Keigo Kurusu or Fourth.
All of these incidents involved,
Yukiteru Amano who's First
and Second, Yuno Gasai."
Twelve individuals
commanded to kill each other.
And if you
don't count Uryuu,
only Seventh, Eighth
and Eleventh remain.
Yes, of course.
Yuki and Yuno are trying to
keep one step ahead of the rest.
The others are gunning for them.
We have got to find
them before they do.
Any promising leads?
They didn't exactly leave us a
trail of bread-crumbs
when they ran off.
We do know they've been taking
trains and other public
transportation.
They were last seen
heading up into the mountains.
I doubt it.
A witness gave us a
positive ID on them both.
Where they were seen, are
there any buildings to speak of?
No, not a one.
The odds of them
being there are very slim.
Smart money says
that they're long gone.
Yuno wouldn't keep running.
There are too many variables
she can't protect Yuki from.
She would go to ground.
Keep going.
That eyewitness you mentioned,
tell me about them.
He was the driver on one
of the buses they took.
Fetch me a map and I need the
particulars of that bus route.
I believe they're
using witnesses
to their own advantage.
But if you're not in the
mountains, then where are you?
Hello, Nishijima.
What's up, guys?
I hope you all got a
good night's sleep.
Should I know this dude, Akise?
Well he did pay for our trip.
Nishijima here gave
me the vouchers.
Did I mention that he's a cop?
--Huh?!
The reason I hooked you up
with the vouchers is because
Yuki and Yuno might be hiding
out in this town somewhere.
Are you serious?!
I want to find Yuki,
but I'm pretty sure
I'm going to need
your help to do it.
Why the hell'd we do that?
Because they can
see into the future.
If I send in cops,
they'll run for it,
and we'll never even
lay eyes on them.
But they won't run
away from friends.
--Sounds like a real drag.
--What's this about?
Is Yuki okay?
I wish I knew.
I'm just running
with Akise's theory.
A, that they're even
in this town, and B,
that she's keeping him prisoner.
Wait, prisoner?!
What would possess
her to do that?!
C'mon, cop!
Tell us the plan!
Well, unfortunately, there
are a number of small towns
near the spot where Yuki
and Yuno were last seen,
and they could be
in any one of them.
This region depends on tourism.
When the economy went south
and the hot springs
weren't as big of a draw,
a lot of the hotels and homes
around here went vacant.
In other words,
she's found the world's
absolute best hiding spot.
So, dude...
This bait-and-switch you
pulled is pretty messed up.
Think of this as payment
for all that crab you ate.
Like it or not,
the fact remains that
Yuki saved all of our asses.
But, how are we
going to find them?
We don't have the first idea
where to start looking.
Well, then, I guess
we'll have to check
every damn building
we come across.
Hold on!
Are you out of your mind?!
You know how long
that's going to take us?!
Poor baby.
Is this too hard for you?
We'll cover more ground
if we split into groups.
Mao, you go with Hinata.
Kousaka, you're with me.
This trip sucks.
Hey, uh, give me a sec.
I got to go take a whiz.
Yeah good luck with that.
Checking every hotel is going to
take a prohibitively long time.
If only we could
shorten this list.
That's Kousaka!
Are you all right?
How I'm I supposed to
wash my hands if there's
no running water in
this stupid place, huh?!
C'mon, man!
Don't make me
draw you a picture!
Running water.
Kousaka, you are a genius!
Hey, Aru.
What you got?
I think I may have
figured out a way to
speed up the process
of finding them.
Remember to tell them the
part where I'm a genius!
Just because they're hiding
doesn't mean they don't
need water and power.
In other words...
We check the lights,
and if they don't work
that means nobody's home!
Yes, in a nutshell.
I think that'll expedite
the dragnet quite a bit.
Also, I'm honor-bound to mention
that Kousaka gave me the idea.
Well, what did they say?!
They must think I'm
pretty frigging awesome,
ain't that right!
I'm glad we don't have
to take the stairs in this one.
My legs could use a break.
The hell's that thing
doing in an elevator?!
It seems she knew we'd opt for
the easier mode of
transportation.
I'm confident that's not the
only trap she's laid out for us.
Dude... let's just
call it a day huh?
I don't think we're going
to find Yuki in this one!
In all likelihood,
your hunch is correct.
But we'll never know for certain
unless we check every last room.
Yuno is nothing
if not meticulous.
She could have him
secreted away anywhere.
Another swing and a miss.
This'd be way easier if we
had some of that diary action.
Keep your chin up.
Look at it this way
every place we cross off
the list gets us that much
closer to finding him.
It's going to work.
Of course it is.
You guys have
covered a lot of ground.
Good job.
I was wondering.
Go on.
This is something of
a long-shot but did
Yuno's family ever own one
of the hotels in the area?
No, that's good!!
That would make sense!
Let me check
and get back to you!
Hey, what's the big idea?!
She's trying to slow us down.
Look alive.
We have to get out of this car.
Yeah but,
how're we going to do it?
I got a text?
How come they
didn't just call me?
This is from Yuki!
What does it say?!
I know where she's keeping him!
Oh crap!
We have to go
get him outta there!
Hold on!
Shouldn't we call the others?!
That'll take too long!
Tell them she's got Yuki
trapped in the basement
of the Grand Hotel!
Thanks, Mao!
Oh Hinata.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Can you hear me?!
Loud and clear.
We just found out
where she's keeping Yuki!
Where are you now?
We should regroup
before we go in.
Hinata went in by herself?
Uh-huh.
Wait, you were saying Hinata
got that text from Yuki, right?
Why would Yuno leave him
his phone if he's her prisoner?
Good point.
Thanks to her diary's powers,
Yuno is privy to every
move that Yuki makes.
He couldn't possibly have sent
that text to Hinata's phone.
No doubt a plea
for help came from
his phone but he was
not the sender.
Damn it!
Yuno sent her a fake message
to lure her into the hotel!
Okay, let's do this.
Hinata's in serious trouble!
That's Hinata's ringtone!
She totally found Yuki
in the hotel basement!
Check it!
So it seems.
But did Hinata send this?
Doubtful.
Yo, guys!
Enough with the
freeze-tag routine!
Let's bust him out already!
Yes, of course.
This way!
Right!
Ready?
Yeah, ready.
Check it, guys.
Yuki.
Twelve o'clock.
Uh, Yuki?
No response.
Perhaps he's unconscious.
Too difficult to tell
from this distance.
I'm going to slip in
and check his condition.
If you could hold the door
open while I do, Kousaka,
I'd be ever so much obliged.
You got it!
I'm your man!
Mao, would you
mind coming with me?
Sure, whenever you're ready.
Hey, Yuki?
Can you hear me?
It's a wig!
Hoist him outta
that chair and let's jam!
Huh?!
No, no, no, no!
You've got to be kidding me!
We cannot be locked in here!
This was a trap.
And we took the bait.
Door's not budging.
We're stuck in here!
But I got that message!
That text wasn't
really from Hinata.
Just like the one that brought
her here in the first place,
it was actually
sent out by Yuno.
But then, where's Hinata?!
Yeah and where's Yuno
hiding the real Yuki?!
Hinata probably made
the same mistake we did,
and came to this room.
Yuno doubtless
got the drop on her.
I hope she's still in one piece.
And what was Yuki
doing during this catfight?!
He just stood by
and let it happen?!
Of course not.
He probably can't move.
What's that hissing?
I know that scent.
It's gas!
Wait, like gas?
--Holy crap!
--No!
If we don't find a
way out of this room,
we're all going to asphyxiate!
You want to make a bet who's
going to win this game, Deus?
Face it...
Team Yuki isn't looking so hot.
I'm putting my money on Second.
What about you, Boss?
I know you like him and all, but
First is out of the running now.
I bet on Yukiteru, regardless.
My faith in the lad has
not wavered one iota.
Mark my words.
First shall prevail.
♪ closing song ♪
Sorry, panties...
No hot spring for you.
Huh?
Dead midget!
Well what have we here?
You're the girl who roused
me from my slumber.
If you hadn't said
something when you did,
I would have remained
asleep for eternity.
So, you got a name?
Who, me?
Yeah, it's uh.
Enough about me!
Since you saved me,
I'll grant you any one
wish your heart desires!
Go nuts, babe!
Make a wish!
I think I'm going to pass.
Oh, and you should
stop napping in baskets.
Not going to lie,
it's kind of weird.
C'mon!
Just make a wish!
I wish I could use
this in the bath.
I think there's
something in the basket.
Dead midget!
Well what have we here?
You're the second girl who
roused me from my slumber.
If you hadn't said
something when you did,
I would have remained
asleep for eternity again.
Uh, what do I call you?
Just call me.
Uh, you know...
But enough about me, right?!
Since you saved me,
I'll grant you any one
wish your heart desires!
Knock it outta the park and go!
A wish?
I don't know.
Wait, wait--don't tell me!
I'm going to use
my powers to
pluck it right outta your head!
You're cutting it way
too close there, Murmur!
Don't give her a chance to turn
you down like the other one did!
Huh?
I think somebody would
really dig a waterproof
cell phone right
about now am I right?
How'd you know
that's what I wanted?!
I rock.
Abracadabra!
Now you can take
pictures in the bath,
with the flash and everything.
Thank you,
wish midget cause now I can!
Uh...
Just don't put them
on the internet.
That's all I'm saying.
I'm going to hit the bath.