I'm not important.
I'm not needed.
I'm a failure.
Nanami!
Where are you?
Where could you be?
Nanami!
Hang in there, Master Mizuki!
What is that supposed to mean?
All I'm doing is
throwing sake around.
Here I am again.
Nowhere to go.
Oh!
I guess since you're making me
do all the hard work that means
you just get to lounge
around on the roof.
Fox-fires, find Nanami!
Nanami?
You mean she's gone?
Wait for me!
I'm coming too!
But Master Mizuki, what about
the miasma at the shrine?
Here you go!
What?
Do what you can with that!
It is impossible!
We cannot do anything!
Oh no!
It is headed toward us!
Back off!
Go away; go away!
Wow!
Oh my--Both familiars
have abandoned their posts.
But what about that miasma?
Well, I could
easily retrieve it.
However, I think I'd rather
just wait and see how things go.
Aren't I the
sweetest wind god ever?
You know I did; you know I did!
Nanami!
Nanami, are you in here?
Master Tomoe!
We have searched everywhere,
but we cannot find
Lady Nanami at all!
We cannot even sense her.
I saw no signs of her
out by the river, either.
Um, yeah, so I didn't see her
over by the station, guys.
We shall continue
to search for her!
Tomoe.
I'm going into town.
Tomoe's finally back at school!
He's dressed like all
traditional, too!
What's the matter, fox?
You stressed out
because you're so late?
Nice outfit.
Well, for someone
with no fashion sense.
What the hell was that, fox?
No one is allowed to ignore me!
Hey, pervert,
this is the girls room.
You can't go in there--
Nanami.
Hey!
What's going on?
I know hostile is your thing,
but this is a bit
much even for you.
Did something happen to Nanami?
This matter is none
of your business.
Hey, Kurama, have you,
by chance, seen Nanami?
We can't find here anywhere.
Sorry; didn't see you there.
Just go.
Okay.
Why do you always
have to be so violent?
Interesting.
Nanami has disappeared.
Since we can't find her after
all the searching we've done,
do you think that maybe
she's left town or something?
No, she has used a talisman.
Please tell me
you have found her.
I've got nothing.
Literally.
I'm running on empty over here.
I am, as well.
Oh, Lady Nanami.
Where in the world
could you be?
Why do I always end up alone?
I'll just go back
to square one!
I mean, me be a god?
Back to square one.
Someone help!
Please, you've gotta help me!
Can you please get
that dog out of here!
I can give you my home.
I don't mind.
You are more worthy
of that house than I am.
Where have you been?
Gone for twenty years?
What could a pathetic
looking thing like her do?
At the most, she might be able
to count the money offerings.
I could not care less if
the shrine goes to ruin.
You're so selfish.
That shrine is your home!
I'm so excited about
the festival this weekend!
What's the name of
that shrine again?
The Mikage Shrine.
Sounds cool.
We should ask Hide and Suzuki
if they wanna go, too!
Totally!
I bet they will!
I so can't wait!
Me either!
What am I doing?
Running away?
That place is my home.
The shrine is my home.
I have to protect it!
Lady Nanami.
Lady Nanami!
There she is!
We found her!
I have to protect the shrine.
At the very least, I can try!
I know I may not succeed,
but only I can do it.
Only me.
I have to do what I
can to save my home!
That is from the
treasure storehouse.
What is this giant miasma?
Oh no!
I dropped the sacred sake!
What is happening?
It looks as though it is drawing
in the rest of the miasma!
Please do not be
what I think it is!
Why?
What do you think it is?
Hold on.
What's happening?
It's a gigantic miasma!
That thing is so
not what I released!
Mayday!
Return, miasma!
Return to this tiny bottle!
The miasma.
Look how big it's grown!
Master Tomoe!
We have found Lady Nanami!
Where is she?
Sir, she is currently
headed back to the shrine.
Back to the shrine?
I'm coming home!
Nanami!
No!
The torii gate!
The shrine!
There is no mistake.
That is the miasma
of the tsuchigumo.
Tsuchigumo?
Do you not remember, Onikiri?
The one Lord Mikage vanquished
several hundred years ago.
That tsuchigumo!
Oh no!
Lord Mikage was able to overcome
it, but its remaining miasma
was far too tainted.
He could not completely
exorcise it, so he decided
to seal it away somewhere.
I suppose this means the
seal was undone, then.
I suppose so but how?
Either way, there is not
anything we can do about it!
Kotetsu!
Max Tailwind!
Lady Nanami!
Go!
Kotetsu!
Lady Nanami!
You have returned to us!
What happened, Kotetsu?
Are you okay?
You must not, Lady Nanami!
We are supernatural beings and
shall be fine, but it would
cause you much harm if you came
into contact with this miasma.
You must not touch me.
You must not.
Kotetsu.
I'm sorry!
I disappeared and
didn't say anything!
Lady Nanami!
You need to know, if this
miasma is allowed to reach town,
it will be disastrous.
Somehow.
Somehow it must be stopped.
Don't worry; I'll protect
the town no matter what.
After all, there are people
looking forward to our festival!
Lady Nanami!
So.
Not that bad?
Where is she?
Nanami.
A tsuchigumo?
It is showing its true form.
That is definitely
a tsuchigumo!
Uh.
Is it just me or is
that thing way scary?
It is not just you!
Nanami, wait!
The tsuchigumo is backing
away from her dance.
Nanami's kagura dance.
There's no hesitation.
Tomoe.
When did she get to be so--?
Lady Nanami is so beautiful.
And so brave!
Look at her.
Yes.
She is lovely to watch.
Mikage?
Right.
Left.
That is perfect.
You remembered well.
Here it comes.
The spot where
you always stumble.
She fell.
Lady Nanami!
Timing.
Ugh.
Lady Nanami!
Tomoe!
Listen to me.
Nanami, you are the girl
I recognize as my
lady and mistress.
You have nothing to fear.
Tomoe!
Nanami!
Your bells!
Mizuki!
I'll help you with
your kagura dance.
Are you ready?
She is fabulous.
Thank goodness.
She is exactly the sort of
girl I believed her to be.
Oh.
Do you mean to say, you,
anticipated this from
the very beginning?
Well.
Who knows?
Nice.
She did it.
Mikage!
Mikage?
Nanami!
Are you hurt?
I did it.
You saw me, didn't you?
Yes.
Lady Nanami!
Look, Kotetsu is also fine!
Oh, good!
What a relief!
I'm happy.
So happy!
Lady Nanami!
Thank you so very much!
Nanami, you are amazing.
Hey, Tomoe.
What is it?
Please, catch me.
After that came the much
anticipated autumn festival!
Oh, looks like
it's very successful.
Well, this shrine
isn't abandoned at all!
Yeah, it's really nice.
I just love the energy.
I can't believe how many
people there are here!
Well, I might have passed
out a handful of flyers.
But all the
festival arrangements.
When did they get done?
We made the preparations.
I brought some lively young
folk to help as well.
We assisted in the preparations.
Himemiko!
Where did you get that outfit?
It's adorable!
You think so?
Hey!
Freshwater fish!
You better not be starting
things without me!
I'm the Dragon King, after all.
It's not a party
until I'm here!
Wow!
You came, Dragon King?
Well, I did get an invitation
from you asking me to come!
And I did so, even though
this festival is held on land
and reeks of mammals!
Reeks of mammals?
Meanwhile, every single one
of you reeks of yokai!
Make some effort to
conceal yourselves!
Oh, fine, what the heck.
Wonderful, now we
all stink like mammals.
Lady Goddess of the land?
We are pleased to
make your acquaintance.
We are the headsmen of the yokai
kind who live to the south.
We are here because
we heard the land god
would perform a kagura dance.
If we bear witness to your
blessed dance, then truly--
It shall spiritually
invigorate us.
We thank you for your blessing.
Good grief.
Please, give me a break ladies.
This is a personal day for me.
Oh, good, looks like
Nanami's been found.
If you don't
wanna be recognized,
maybe don't dress so flashy.
Hey, shopkeeper.
Can I get a mask?
Sure thing!
This one here is
called a death mask.
Guess what it can do!
I hear it shows
your face in death.
You can keep the change.
Was that guy human?
Lady Nanami!
It is time for
your kagura dance!
Oh.
Right.
We are going to prepare
for you to get changed!
We shall be waiting for you!
'Kay!
I managed it in front
of the tsuchigumo.
But dancing in front of an
audience of people makes
me nervous in a
completely different way.
You'll be fine, little girl.
Hey!
You're that he-she guy.
Who are you calling he-she guy?
Here you are; I bought
these sweets in town.
They're for you.
Oh, what for?
For knowing you can do
the dance magnificently.
So long, little girl!
Let's meet again sometime!
Look!
There she is!
So pretty!
Nice.
That night, the festival reached
its zenith and brilliantly
lit up the hearts of all who
were blessed enough to be there.
I am glad the festival
was such a success!
The rumors that the
Mikage shrine is abandoned
will surely fade away now.
You did perfect, Nanami, and
your kagura dance was beautiful.
Oh, thank you, Mizuki.
But my back is killing me.
Ow.
Well, on the bright side,
we're sure to get some
more worshippers now.
True!
Boo.
We're all out of sake.
I'll go get some more.
You know, we can prepare
something delicious
to serve along with it, as well.
Onikiri?
Right!
So, tell me what you
thought about my dancing.
Yes.
Quite an achievement.
You did well.
And anything else?
Anything else?
That is all.
There's nothing else?
Really?
'Cause Mizuki said he
thought it was beautiful.
Guess not, though.
It was beautiful.
More beautiful than anything.
What did you say?
Speak up; I couldn't hear you.
Yes you could; you
heard me just fine.
Come on!
Maybe just one more time!
Oh, shut up.
Okay, I heard you.
I'm happy.
Nanami.
May I seal the familiar
contract with you?
What?
But the familiar contract--
It is from the heart.