It's raining.
Can this be over yet?
You guys!
Check it out, it's a snake!
Seriously?
The Snake.
Dude, it's like albino!
We should find something
to put him in.
It's always a good day when
a snake shows up at school.
Hey, maybe he could
be the new mascot!
Leave it alone!
White snakes are said to
be messengers of the gods.
You guys are risking
divine retribution.
She's touching a snake!
There get home.
This isn't a safe
place for you.
Hey Nanami, you might
want to check to see
if your hand's okay.
It's fine, he didn't
bite me or anything.
Look at your arm!
It's all red!
Now that's kind of
disturbing, isn't it?
Welcome home, Lady Nanami.
We have missed you!
Where's Tomoe?
Preparing you a
lovely evening meal!
Please tell me those aren't
mushrooms I'm smelling in there.
I wonder if your lack of good
taste might be a reflection
of your intelligence when
it comes to white talismans.
What is this?
Have you seen your arm?
Where did this mark come from?
Um, I picked up a snake at
school and I guess I must
be allergic to them?
On the contrary, the snake
has left its Mark Of Favor.
What does that mean?
To put it in simple terms,
it means that he has chosen
you to become his wife.
He did what?
I think you heard me.
Now what I want to know is how
did you become so affectionate
with the snake in question?
A white snake wanders into
the school and is attacked.
And then you stepped in
and rescued him from harm.
How heroic.
I wish you could have seen him!
He was beautiful!
Well, he will be coming for you
soon so I will at least be able
to catch a glimpse
before you go.
Oh good then you can-- wait!
'Coming for me?'
Correct!
Your heedlessness has resulted
in your betrothal to a snake!
But no need to worry.
I will not allow anyone to lay
a finger or scale on you.
If I lose my lady and
mistress to a snake,
it will be a black mark
upon my reputation.
Although, a white snake will
not be so easy to defeat.
How did I get myself into this?
So are you sure you can pull
this whole student thing off?
Positive.
I read the entire
booklet last night.
This is not good.
It amazes me how many
dramatic scenarios
you are able to create.
Look if you don't
want to be here,
I'm pretty sure I can
deal with a tiny snake.
Listen to me.
Do not stray from my side for
a moment while we are here.
Is that clear?
Yeah.
Class, I'd like you to meet
our new transfer student.
This is Tomoe Mikage.
So.
Let's find you an open seat.
That one.
This is happening.
Tomoe's in my class.
Not exactly how I thought
things would turn out.
So, the Tengu is absent?
I think he must be busy
with work this week.
Ya know, usually days
when Kurama isn't here
are pretty quiet, not today.
Tomoe, right?
I think I remember you!
Yeah, didn't you bring lunch
for the class one time?
That was sweet.
That's gonna get old.
I know it's kinda been awhile,
but do you remember us?
I'm sure we were the hottest
girls in class that day!
There's no way
he remembers them.
Come on.
How could I forget?
Natsuko Umibe, Megumi Tobita,
Chie Kitami.
I know the names and faces
of everyone in this class,
especially you three.
I put in extra effort
for Nanami's friends.
It seemed right.
Okay.
So, is she like your
girlfriend or something?
Nanami is my mistress and--
You can't say things like that
to regular people, Tomoe!
It kinda freaks them out!
Like what?
What did I say?
Are you serious?
Nanami is my mistress and I'm
her manservant!" That kind of
crap sounds like we have
something kinky going on
and everyone will
make fun of me!
Here's the deal: you're the son
of a wealthy foreign family
that's taken me in and that's
why you used those terms.
Sorry to interrupt.
The teacher asked me to
give you the class daybook.
Here ya go.
Oh.
Thanks, Ami.
Looks like a stinker of a list.
See ya!
So, do you think
she overheard us?
Is that another
friend of yours?
I think that's the second
time I've ever spoken to her.
That was strange.
Miss Nanami is kind of
an odd duck sometimes.
But even though I'm still
a little weirded out over
what happened last week, I
really hope we can be friends.
How strange.
I don't think we've ever spent
this much time together before.
Not even when we're
at the shrine.
It's nice.
I feel like we're
actually becoming closer.
There, I think
that's all of it!
Sorry that took so long!
I just have to drop it off
and we can go!
Looks like today
kinda got to him.
It was nice having him here.
I think I could
get used to this.
Miss Nanami.
It's good to see you.
What a lovely day for rain.
Oh yeah.
I'd completely
forgotten about that.
Nanami!
Please, have a look
Lady Yonomori.
The plum tree has finally
started to blossom.
Mizuki, is there no one
special in your life with whom
you can share these flowers?
No, miss.
Of course not.
You'll find her someday.
Please promise to
tell me when you do.
Tomoe!
There you are!
Don't tell me you go
straight home after school?
You should come with us.
We're going shopping.
Fox Fire!
Bring me Nanami!
Damn white snake.
When I find you, I will
slice you into sashimi!
No wake?
No wake.
That looks like waking!
Hello, human!
You want a centipede?
Good morning, Miss Nanami.
Thank you for rescuing me at
your school the other day.
You're that guy!
I was walking home and
we talked and then---
My name is Mizuki.
I am the familiar here.
Welcome.
Our life together will be rich.
Our life?
Joyful day!
Master Mizuki has
taken you as his bride!
Time to start the
wedding happenings!
Welcome to the family, human!
Whoa!
Nobody ever asked me if
I wanted to get married!
It seems you have met
our two shrine spirits.
And right behind you, taking
a rest through those doors
is the god of this shrine.
Lady Yonomori.
She is very private.
A god's in there?
Miss Yonomori has given her
blessing upon this marriage
and sends her welcome.
Come, my lovely bride.
Stop that.
I'm not getting married
to anyone right now!
Perhaps you are confused.
The mark on your wrist
denotes our engagement.
I know it seems sudden, my dear.
I'm leaving!
Well, if you must try, you must.
Good luck getting out.
What's wrong with those guys?
I'm going home no matter what!
Seriously.
Do they think I've never
walked out of a shrine before?
In your face, freaks!
Not as tough as
you thought it was!
Jerks.
I don't know exactly where I am,
but--I think if I just keep
following this road it will
lead to a familiar highway
or something at least.
It has to!
Damn it!
You're not going to confuse me!
I'm going home!
Those are people up there!
Maybe they can give me
directions!
Glad you found your way back.
Welcome home, my dear.
But how--how'd this happen?
I walked all that way.
Yes, I tried to
warn you about that.
If you are not
entirely worn out,
go ahead and give
it another try.
This is crazy.
What a horrible person.
Oh no.
Your leg is bleeding.
Hold still.
We have to take care
of it right away!
This might sting.
I will not allow anyone to lay
a finger or scale on you.
He lied.
Please do not cry.
There is no reason to be sad.
You have a brand new
life here, now.
Lady Yonomori said you
can stay here forever.
I give you my vow, Nanami.
I will treat you much
better than Tomoe ever did.
It's not even the right season
for plum blossoms
but they're blooming.
This isn't like the
real world, is it?
It's true.
The plum tree is now
as it will always be.
I stopped time when it was
at its most beautiful.
Somewhere in spring.
The blossoms are Lady
Yonomori's favorite flower.
Would you like
to go to bed soon?
What?
I'm not going to try anything.
You can stay here
until you feel up to it.
Rest and gather your strength.
Beddy-by!
Tomoe.
Can you hear my thoughts?
If you're my familiar,
please hurry up and save me.
Part two coming right up!
Lady Nanami!
Oh Lady Nanami
has been abducted!
She has been taken
from us and forced
into being the
bride of a snake!
This shrine is done for!
Do not cry, Onikiri.
There is hope.
Behold!
Master Tomoe is
so calm and composed!
Ever since he returned,
he has been relaxing
and polishing that bottle.
Not a sign of stress
or worry, whatsoever!
He is truly the world's
greatest familiar, is he not?
I bet he already has a plan!
It is so reassuring!
Bad luck!
The shrine is done for!
Shut up, you are
making my head swell!
I never imagined that
I would fail so miserably.
I am sick with worry.
With her lack of physical
strength, I doubt she could
defend herself
were she attacked.
She must be terrified.
I let her slip from
my grasp unattended.
I will find her.
No matter what it takes.
Mizuki?
It's a wonderful shrine.
The god who lives here
has everything she could
want--a familiar,
shrine spirits,
and yet-- There's something--
Something not quite right.
It's breakfast time!
Yummy breakfast time!
Munchings and crunchings
for the human god!
Are you crazy?
I'm not eating that!
Taking care of a human
takes some getting used to.
Our Lady Yonomori
only partakes of sake.
Master Mizuki makes the bestest
sake in the entire world!
And one time, Lady Yonomori
even said that Master Mizuki
is the world's
greatest familiar.
I say that about Tomoe.
His cooking is flawless and
the shrine spirits there
are perfectly well-behaved.
Unlike you rabid brats.
Ah, so he is a
culinary artist as well?
Yes, he's the best there is.
Have you ever heard of him?
Of course, my dear.
In fact, I've known him
a lot longer than you have.
He is a white fox
of a lowly origin.
I've heard just about
enough out of you jerks!
This marks yet another
disaster for Tomoe.
Once again, he's carelessly
lost the god he serves.
I can just see him
sitting despondently
on the outer corridor.
Pathetic.
Oh, whatever.
You're the pathetic one.
He's probably out looking
for me as we speak.
This shrine seems to
be missing something.
Mizuki.
You said that no one comes
to visit this shrine anymore
but how long ago
did people stop coming?
I'm going to have to
think about that one.
Hey!
Don't go in there!
You mustn't touch
Lady Yonomori!
I knew it!
This shrine doesn't
even have a god!
I think it's about time you
tell me what's going on here.
Master Tomoe.
We have found it.
The village you
seek is down there.
A dam.
It is unlikely
that either humans
or gods still remain there.
A water god's shrine
submerged underwater.
How humorous.
Master Tomoe.
Does this mean Lady Nanami
is trapped under there?
I have known of many
white snake familiars but
there is only one sheltered,
naive fool among them that
would ever entertain the idea
of making a human god his bride.
Because of this, I now
know exactly where she is.
A long time ago,
there was a large river
right near where we are.
Children would
often get swept away.
So the villagers built this
shrine because they feared
that their land was cursed.
Thankfully we are
still standing.
Gods like Lady Yonomori
came into being because
the humans needed them.
Likewise, gods cannot maintain
their presence without humans.
When the humans abandoned
this land, Lady Yonomori went
into hiding and we haven't
seen her since then.
But I won't abandon it.
I'll stay and protect
the shrine and her,
because that's the
duty of the familiar.
He's here, alone, in this
hollowed out shell of a shrine.
Serving a lady and mistress
who will never return.
His loyalty is touching.
All this time, you've been
lonely here, haven't you?
Tell me the truth.
Um, I mean, I've kinda been
doing the god thing, too,
for a while so I can relate.
I have a familiar that I
care about who's amazing.
I couldn't stand it if
Tomoe were feeling as sad
and lonely as you are.
It would kill me.
If I had to leave,
I wouldn't want him to be
sitting around the shrine.
I'd want him out in the world,
living his life.
I bet that Yonomori would
feel the same exact way.
Check it out.
When Mikage quit being a god,
Tomoe was a complete mess,
hanging out in the
red light district.
You could be doing that, too!
I mean, if that's what you want.
Maybe it's not but
you get the point.
Are you trying to comfort me?
What a kind heart you have,
Miss Nanami.
You must understand why I
need you to stay here with me
for the rest of our lives.
It would be just the two of us.
We could spend every day
enjoying the plum blossoms.
Together.
Forever.
I'm so sorry.
I can't live here
with you forever.
I have people who are waiting
for me to come home, like Tomoe.
I'm sure he's out there
now looking for me.
No, please.
Please love me.
Get off me!
What's wrong with you?
You said you weren't going
to try anything with me!
I know but we are closer now.
No wait!
Please, don't.
Help me, Tomoe!
You dare to lay a hand
on my lady and mistress?
I hope you are prepared to pay
severely for what you have done!
You found me!
Step away from her!
Nanami!
You're safe now, thank goodness.
You're late.
I must say, I'm impressed.
I never imagined
you'd find this place.
And you're still as
ill mannered as ever, Tomoe.
The fire!
Trying to burn down
a water god's shrine?
My, how flagrantly sacrilegious.
Well, you are a former fox,
so I guess it makes sense.
Tell me.
Do you actually intend
to try to battle me here?
Because that would
be embarrassing.
You realize you
started out as a yokai
and I'm a divine familiar?
Ordinarily, your kind
wouldn't even be allowed
to speak with me,
let alone fight.
There's a social hierarchy
for familiars, too?
A water god's shrine.
You sure about that?
You see, I already know your
water god and your shrine
are long crumbled into nothing.
This is an artificial space
that you created to play
at being a familiar.
Because of that idiocy,
I had a lot of trouble
finding this place.
And now, Master Former Divine
Familiar-- The time has come
for you to pay for trying
to steal my lady and mistress!
Extinguish!
It is no use.
The Fox Fire is already hard
at work tearing this
place down on all sides.
If you never gave me
a reason to find you,
you would still
have your shrine.
Loss one.
I am taking Nanami back with me
so I guess you lost your bride.
Loss two.
Loss three will be your life.
Master Mizuki!
Our house is on fire!
Listen to me, Mizuki.
I'm not going to die.
I am simply returning to nature.
However, I worry for you.
Swear to me on this plum tree.
That even after I have vanished,
You will never cry alone.
Thank goodness it's all right.
I see.
So this tree has served
as your cornerstone.
The shrine and everything
else surrounding it was
originally placed as a
distraction to keep it safe.
You're right.
This is all I have left now,
Lady Yonomori's tree.
It's the most precious thing
I own because she loved it.
Can you understand, Tomoe?
As a fellow familiar?
I can.
Completely.
Tomoe.
So well that it hurts.
Which is why it would be my
ultimate pleasure to burn it
to cinders as payment
for your foolish crimes!
No!
Please don't!
Somewhere in spring.
The blossoms are Lady
Yonomori's favorite flower.
We could enjoy them,
every day, together.
Forever.
Tomoe.
That's enough, okay?
Mizuki?
So yeah, Tomoe's finally
come to get me and I'll be
going home now.
I'm sorry I couldn't
stay here forever with you
like you wanted, but--
I'll make you a promise.
If you feel lonely
here by yourself.
I'll come back to visit you
and the plum blossoms.
Any time.
So, does this mean that
you're going to be upset?
No.
Why would I be upset?
Because you were too
friendly with a snake?
Because you promised to see him
again right in front of me?
No, of course not!
He could have just said yes.
Look, don't get angsty.
He's there by himself.
What if I were to die suddenly?
What if you were left here
alone just like him?
It would break my heart and
I would hope someone
would come to visit you.
That's why I made the promise.
Irrelevant.
You were hurt?
Oh.
Yeah, I just tripped.
It's okay now, though.
I am very sorry.
This is all because
I let you out of my sight.
She merely trips and she bleeds.
It pains me to think what
might happen if she were
to fall from a tree.
How perilous to think
such a fragile creature
is my cornerstone.
I am confounded.
This is more than I can handle.
Whatever, let's go home.
I must keep from ruining this
and keep myself from ruin.
The God of Thunder, Lady
Narukami, is about to strike!
She steals Nanami's mark
of godhood and then attacks
Tomoe with a Lucky Mallet!
That means he shrinks!
Believe me, you won't
want to miss it!
Look how cute he is!
Next time, "The God Loses
Her Home." Poor darling.