This is the second day
I've been back at the shrine.
And I've felt kind of weird
ever since yesterday.
Nanami.
Good morning.
What is wrong?
Your face is red.
Shut up!
No it's not!
This wasn't how it
was supposed to be.
Since then, I've been alone here
with my heart in my throat.
Is it bland?
Soy sauce?
No, thanks.
It makes me a little mad.
I mean, he's a fox, right?
Stay cool.
Keep it together.
As I suspected.
You are ill and have a fever.
No way.
Thirty-nine point eight!
What a high temperature!
Please stay home from
school, Lady Nanami!
I wish I could.
But I'll be fine.
Besides, my attendance record
is hanging on the edge.
If I have any more absences,
I'll have to repeat the year.
Master Tomoe!
You have to stop her!
No, let me go.
I cannot allow you to go to
school in your current state.
This will be good.
Take time off from something
as unimportant as school.
Yeah, well just because
it's not godly doesn't
mean it's not important!
I'd also like to mention that
you're touching my hand!!
Trust me, I am saying this with
your best interests at heart.
In that case, why not change
yourself into Lady Nanami?
Then, you could
go to school for her,
and she will not have
to have an absence!
That's a great idea!
And so, Nanami Momozono
will be taking the liberty of
skipping her classes today.
Yay.
I feel like poo.
Don't tell me
Nanami's out again today!
No way she's not
gonna get held back.
Anyone wanna bet on whether
Nanami comes back to school?
Starting at three hundred!
Isobe.
Why do you get so excited
about anything Nanami?
Are you sure that you
don't have a crush on her?
Are you kidding me?
Poor and daddy issues are
not exactly my style, bro!
She's just too
easy to laugh at.
Huh?
Sorry to bother you, but I
believe you are in my seat.
Would you mind moving?
Wait.
What?
Is that really Nanami?
I don't get it.
What's with that
aura around her?
Dude, is it just me, or did
her boobs get bigger, too?
Curse you, Nanami.
I will be certain to make
you pay for this atrocity.
Morning everyone.
For the first time in a week.
The famous and talented pop
star Kurama has returned
to your class.
The tengu!
I've brought you a souvenir.
Nanami.
What's wrong?
You seem to have become
more womanly since
the last time I saw you.
Nice rack.
Foolish tengu.
My transformation
spell is perfect.
This school day is
sure to be a breeze.
What?
The fox goes here?
Yeah.
All the girls were
freaking out about it, too.
I think he's out
sick today, though.
Don't worry, Kurama.
I think you're like, so
much cooler than that guy.
I made a copy of
my notes for you.
I mean, if you want 'em.
Seriously?
Damn it.
I swear, I go away for a week,
and the whole
school falls apart.
I had planned on using the
time Nanami would be away
from the fox to
grow closer to her.
Apparently, I don't
have much time to waste.
Okay, next page.
Read from the top, if you would?
Nanami?
What the hell is this writing?
Cat got your tongue?
Read it now, please.
If I may.
Nanami's been sick, so she
can't speak very loudly.
Although I can read it for her.
All night their course lay
through intricate defiles
and over irregular
and rock-strewn paths.
More than once they lost
their way, but Hope's
intimate knowledge of the
mountains enabled them
to regain the track once more.
He's always just so cool.
Even his speaking
voice is like whoa.
Did you enjoy that, Nanami?
Okay?
Second Period
All right, please stop,
Miss Momozono.
You're the only one
who's out of tune.
Try it again by yourself.
♪ Radiant like the
sun shining in the-- ♪
I hate to say it, but that part
just isn't working quite right.
I do have a thought.
Why don't we have a
professional singer show us
how it should be done?
Sure thing.
♪ Radiant like the sun shining
in the sky with wings
of purest white...
In the embrace of
joyous rapture, I soar...
in euphoria.
Hallelujah!
Everything is living here,
within my song to you.
Kiss me.
Kiss you. ♪
He's singing
right in front of me!
I'm gonna die.
I'm dying!
Lame.
I thought this
was a choral piece.
Do you like my singing, Nanami?
Kay.
What?
Nanami.
What's wrong?
You seem like you're
in a bad mood, today.
Ya' know, if something's
bothering you,
you can always
talk to me about it.
I will say this
to you only once.
You suck.
Do not follow me around.
I know you are after my
heart quite literally.
For that is the way to
obtain my status as a god.
So, back off.
Oh, no.
Is that's what you've
been agonizing about.
Well, I'm sorry
you thought that.
But you've got me all wrong.
Why is he touching her?
Oh, the horror!
I will tell you what
I really desire.
Your love.
Touch me again and you die.
I can't believe you
hit me in the face.
Nanami.
I wanted to mention
something to you.
In all seriousness,
it has to do with the
miasma in the air here.
It's grown heavier.
Don't go into dark
spaces by yourself.
Miasma?
Yes.
There is definitely a
heavier presence than before.
Darkness is the entrance
to the world over yonder.
The miasma's must mean that
an entrance is open nearby.
Apparently, the tengu is not
as asinine as I thought.
Ami!
Hurry up, or we're
gonna be late!
Yeah, I know;
hold on just a sec.
I can't find my headband.
I could swear it's in here.
You're so slow.
I'll just meet you there!
Come on.
Kei, you turned
the lights off on me!
You know how dark it and
scary it gets down here!
Are you still there?
Oh no; I'm in here by myself.
Stupid basement
and it's no windows,
I can't see anything at all.
Oh.
Kei, I hate you!
Who's a cute, cute little girl?
Does she have the sweet,
sweet taste of candy?
What flavor are you, precious?
I lick.
Strawberry!
Yummy!
Someone!
Help!
Finally.
There you are.
Oh, Nanami, I saw a ghost!
A ghost!
There was a ghost
and it licked my face!
And then it told me I
tasted like strawberries!
Yes, I know.
It is a visitor
from over yonder.
I want you to go on
ahead to class.
What are you gonna do?
Finish some business in here.
How so?
Leave.
Get out.
Ami!
The teacher's here already!
Kei!
Wait for me!
Could you be any slower?
You and Nanami are the only
ones who haven't shown up
to class yet.
Was she in the locker room
with you while you were
taking like forever?
Still is.
Go on without me!
Ami?
I like this place a lot.
So many girls come in here and
just take off their clothes.
All I did was watch; technically
I didn't do anything wrong.
Surely you understand.
Surely you won't burn me!
A perverted low-level yokai.
Nothing that should merit
my personal attention;
however for Nanami.
I must eliminate all
future problems when I can.
What a bother.
Nanami wait!
I lick!
Why do you have no flavor!
You are not tasty!
Hold it!
I hate the tasteless!
Hello, Strawberry Flavor!
I lick!
That's enough.
Wow, Kurama; it's you!
I thought that I told you to
stay away from dark places.
Nanami.
It hurts; it hurts.
Kurama!
Take that child and
go outside immediately!
Uh, so do you have any
idea what that thing is?
Don't worry about it; you should
really just get back to class.
Yeah, but Nanami is in there!
Will you do me a favor?
Can what happened
today be a secret?
Promise me you
won't tell anyone?
Kay.
Coming in.
What happened to that yokai?
Did you let it go?
Yes, of course you did.
I guess that's fine.
But be careful.
Unlike the fox, I can't always
be by your side to protect you.
Don't do anything reckless.
Not without him near.
Then starting tomorrow,
I must be sure to have Tomoe
come with me.
You want this?
Don't worry!
The next part
is coming right up!
This is a soft shell turtle
that we caught recently!
Partaking of soft shell turtle
stew is sure to cure Lady Nanami
of her nasty cold!
Nanami, do you honestly mean
to tell me you've
been eating turtles?
I wonder why Tomoe has you
on such a bizarre diet.
And I wonder.
Hey, what are you doing in
our kitchen anyway, Mizuki?
What?
I heard a rumor Tomoe wasn't
going to be here today.
So I decided to come see you.
Then, your shrine
fellows spirits asked me
to make you lunch.
That hurts!
Oh, the soft shell turtle
bit Master Mizuki's finger!
We must get water!
While Tomoe was at
school disguised as Nanami.
Mizuki, the familiar
of the Yonomori Shrine,
was visiting Nanami.
Really?!
Tomoe crossed-dressed as
you and went to school?!
Right now, I'm more
concerned about the turtle,
put him in that boiling
water and you will die!
I guess your Sacred Word
Binding must be very powerful.
It's not like I ordered him.
I just asked him to go,
and he went.
You asked him, did you?
Tomoe must be
putting on quite
the innocent familiar
act around you.
What does that mean?
Well he was a wild
fox to begin with.
So as his mistress, you need
to lead him with a firm hand.
Mizuki.
I don't appreciate you
talking about Tomoe like that.
He doesn't
deserve to be judged,
not because of his looks
or where he came from.
You'll just have to believe me.
I spend more time with him,
and I know him the best.
Sure he seems
kind of wild sometimes.
But he does have
a gentle side, too.
Oh, no.
It seems you've been
completely finessed by him.
His abilities are
stronger than I thought.
Familiars are
supposed to serve gods.
But unfortunately you appear
to be the one who
was tamed instead.
Trust me, if you
let your guard down,
that beast will
kill you in your sleep.
Trust me!
I say Tomoe isn't like that!
Nanami, you are
far too stubborn.
You are!
Perhaps you need to go take
a peek with your own eyes.
See Tomoe.
And his true colors.
Master Mizuki, what kind
of burner is this?
Oh.
A time-wending incense burner.
It's a votive object that
transports the soul to the past.
Far in the past, before
you were even born.
There you'll find a Tomoe
you may not even recognize.
How could I not
recognize Tomoe?
Lady Nanami?
She's fine.
She's on her way now.
Off to have fun in
the crevices of time.
Go take a peek.
Far into the past.
Before you were born.
Discover a Tomoe
before he knew you.
Oh, ow.
Like I would ever
not recognize Tomoe.
I swear, I'm gonna
kill Mizuki for this.
Hold on.
That's weird.
When did my hands get so tiny?
And my clothes.
My hair?
No.
But how?!
This is not my body!
Oh yeah!
This has to be the
world inside my dreams.
Someone help.
It hurts.
A little boy.
I'm here.
What happened?
You can't go back there.
We were attacked by some yokai.
They killed everyone,
in the village.
They killed everyone.
Yokai?
Akura-oh is looking for you;
I can't believe he hasn't
caught you already.
I, I ran away
as fast as I could.
That bastard killed them all.
Akura-oh?
A yokai is looking for me?
Is this really a dream?
Lucky for us, this
empty house was nearby.
Goodness.
It's really coming down, huh?
At least we'll be dry in here.
I need to treat his injury.
Who would inflict such a
terrible wound on a child?
I'm more lucky, I think.
Who'd have guessed you'd just
happen to be out of the village,
working in the fields.
Such a fine virgin,
there's no way Lord Akura-oh
would pass over
something like you.
He always takes every prey
of any value away from us,
you know.
A yokai?
This is bad.
Don't worry about
Lord Akura-oh.
I'll devour you long
before he gets here!
Someone help!
Lord.
Tomoe.
I.
That was foxfire.
Trash always does burn well.
My, a village girl?
Tomoe?
It is true; you are
quite a fine specimen.
Rather awful hamlet, though.
Tomoe?
Lovely voice.
Cry out.
Human.
This isn't him.
This isn't Tomoe!
Tell me.
Who are you?
Tomoe!
Tomoe.
You disappear on me for what?
A rundown shack in the woods?
Someone's here.
This is my chance to get away.
I have no wish to get wet.
You're not very good company.
I came because I heard
there was a beauty here.
But the village only had
old hags and ugly women.
Even some of those
cows escaped from me.
I suppose she must have
slipped away with them.
You mean a little girl
gave you the slip?
You are losing your touch.
Akura-oh.
I don't suppose you've seen
her in the area, have you?
They call her Yukiji.
No.
He was a wild fox
to begin with.
If you let your guard down.
He's wrong.
That beast will
kill you in your sleep.
He's wrong!
Of course.
This is only a dream.
Nanami.
You were gone for
a terribly long time.
Where am I?
Your home at the shrine.
Lady Nanami, it took you
so very long to awaken.
We were so worried!
I'm exhausted.
But wasn't I sleeping?
No.
I sent your soul into the past,
so you were actually awake.
You experienced the
world of the past,
which leads to our present.
Did you meet Tomoe, by chance?
No.
I didn't see him.
See whom?
Who were you not able to see?
Why is there a snake
loitering in the shrine?
Hey there, Tomoe!
Welcome home!
Did you have
fun at school today?
What the hell
are you doing here?
What were you doing to Nanami?
I.
Can't.
Tell.
You.
Get out!
That damn snake!
Why did you let him
into the shrine?
We had thought to serve
soft shell turtle stew
to Lady Nanami.
What does a turtle stew
have to do with him?!
Nanami.
Your temperature.
It is still high.
I will make you
something for it.
Stay in bed.
That's the touch I know.
The gentle touch
of Tomoe's hand.
What is wrong?
What did Mizuki do to you?
No, nothing; I just
had a nightmare.
I'll be okay, though.
Thanks Tomoe.
I'm so glad the Tomoe
I know is this Tomoe.
More importantly,
how was your day?
Did you have fun at school?
Tomoe is pretty comfortable
with life at school.
After all, he is popular
among the female students.
Even Nanami's heart tends
to race rather quickly.
Now is when
you should work up
the courage to
move forward, lady!
Next time, "The God Asks
a Boy Out on a Date."
Wanna maybe go to the
aquarium together?