What a shame.
I've been slaving away,
brewing this latest batch
of sacred sake, but Nanami's
too busy hanging out with Tomoe
at school to even try it.
That fox gets to be around
her twenty-four-seven,
and I can't even tag along.
Life as her familiar
is downright unfair.
This is truly excellent!
Your sacred sake is
certainly something else!
Crisp, smooth, and
so full of flavor!
Surely no other shrine has
sacred sake that can compare!
It's my best brew yet but
I can't exactly call it
"sacred" sake until
Nanami drinks it.
Why is it that I'm always stuck
at the shrine with you guys
while Tomoe's allowed
to go to school with her?
It's not like I'm some useless
yokai; I can do stuff, too!
What's it going to take for
Nanami to finally notice
that I exist.
Master Mizuki, you are still
unaccustomed to human society.
Perhaps Lady Nanami wishes
to wait until you are better
acquainted with humans.
If you ask me, I think
I'm plenty used to them.
But how do I convince Nanami
to feel the same way?
Well, here is one example.
♪ Gleaming like stars
against the midnight sky
With wings of deceit
In the embrace of joyous
rapture, I fall into delirium! ♪
If you were accustomed
to humans to this degree,
I doubt Nanami would object.
You have got to be kidding!
Why would so many humans want
to worship that scumbag?
Master Kurama has lived among
and performed in front
of humans for seventeen years.
Lady Nanami herself was once
crazy about him just like
the other human girls.
Say it isn't so!
A Tengu that leaves its
mountain temple doesn't receive
divine favor and as a result
can't cast powerful spells.
I wonder what kind of
yokai powers he's using.
Interesting.
Since things are boring
here anyway, I'm gonna go pay
Kurama a little visit
and pick his brain.
If all goes well, Nanami will be
changing her tune in no time!
Behold, Mizuki arrives
at the great metropolis!
A massive concrete jungle!
Where you can witness crowds
upon crowds of busy people
going about their day!
This is the city?
I don't remember all
this negative energy
floating around
when I last visited.
Then again,
it has been a while.
I suppose it is not known as the
"demon capital" for nothing.
No matter.
Kurama's supposed to be
at a place called Toranomon.
Is everything all right,
Master Mizuki?
Of course!
It's not like this place
is just crawling with
demons out to get you.
Hello sir!
Are you looking for some help?
So you see, dear friend, it was
the will of God that brought us
together on this blessed day!
The heavenly Father sent us to
make you happy, oh so happy!
You do want to be happy,
don't you?
This is your path
to finding happiness
for the rest of your days!
With a generous donation
you can take the first step
towards lifelong happiness!
The bigger the donation
the better, as the number
of blessings God infuses into
the sticker is directly related
to how much money you give!
Donate enough and you can even
wipe away all of your sin!
Hallelujah!
Well?
Do we have a deal?
The demon capital,
without a doubt.
Talk about scary.
Even Isohime wouldn't
be that demanding!
We ended up spending all of the
offering money from the shrine.
Now, where is
Toranomon located?
Maybe the local
humans can help me!
Hey you guys, over here!
Would you know where
I could find Toranomon?
Who da hell do ya think ya are?
Ya tryin' ta get yourself
shot or somethin?
What do you mean?
Are you threatening me, sir?
A snake!
There's a giant snake
around that boy's shoulders!
Oh no!
Master Mizuki!
Let's get out of here!
Hey, come back here!
What's with this place?
Nothing seems to go right;
it's like it's out to get you!
I gotta soldier through
for Nanami's sake.
Wait a second,
isn't that Nanami's?
Is this a joke?
A sticker's not gonna cut it,
I only take cold hard cash!
What?
But that's all I've--
Come on.
Cough it up, kid.
If you aren't gonna pay me,
then I'm gonna have
to call the police!
Oh, what do I do now?
Hey.
What's a little snake doing
in a big city like this?
Kurama.
At last!
I've found you!
Please give me five thousand
eight hundred and forty yen!
What are you talking about?
You've come an awfully long way.
Running errands for Nanami?
Actually, I came
here to see you.
Kurama!
Let's get going!
We've got that television
wrap party happening at six!
You know you can't miss it!
My reputation as your
manager would be ruined
if you stood these people up!
Is this a buddy of yours
I haven't met yet?
No.
Yes, I wanted
to pay him a visit.
Well then, you should absolutely
come to the wrap party with him!
Oh, these things have
the best food in the world!
Hey, shut it.
Wrap party?
That sounds really fun!
Come see for yourself!
Whose manager are you?
Disgusting.
The food wasn't cooked
with your tastes in mind.
So, what is a familiar
from Mikage Shrine doing
so far away from home?
I could ask you the same thing.
Why do you live in
a place like this?
I walked around town
the whole day.
The entire city's covered
in this negative aura.
The people are
so mean and cruel.
I can barely breathe here, so I
can't imagine living here, too.
It's just sickening to me.
The cycle of negativity's
just too much for me to handle.
Then why come?
I'm just saying.
I wouldn't do something
like abandon my own shrine.
Especially not
for this tainted city.
Then run back home
to the shrine already.
You're not cut out
for this place.
Ah, there you are!
You must say hello
to Miss Tayama.
Was the Tengu just
making fun of me?
Master Mizuki,
let us return home.
What drink do ya got there?
Is that carrot juice?
How cute.
It tastes like grief
and disappointment.
What about yours?
Right here's my seventh
glass of this stuff.
A toast to when this pansy
finally turns twenty-one!
I know my way around
drinks as well.
This is my most recent
brew of sacred sake.
Woah, my bad,
you got a babyface!
Lemme introduce
ya to my friend.
She's a cocktail that looks
delicate but packs a punch!
Down the hatch!
My daughter is
a huge fan of yours.
She'll be so jealous when I let
her know I met Kurama in person.
Mind if I have a closer look?
It's not every day that I have
the honor of being called upon
by a legendary actress.
You flatter me.
Here ma'am!
Excuse me, but here's
the drink ya asked for.
Sorry for the wait!
What is that swill?
Can you not see that I am
holding a dessert in my hand?
A sugary spirit like that will
do nothing to cleanse my palate!
Couldn't you have grabbed
something more appropriate?
My apologies!
I'll be right back with
somethin' else for ya!
And don't you dare
keep me waiting!
Who's that?
One of the worst
assistants I've ever had.
But that's what I get for being
kindhearted to a commoner
from the country.
Her goal is to
become an actress.
Thinking about it
makes me want to laugh!
Home.
I wanna go home.
I feel so bad.
Someone kill me.
Kurama was right.
I'm just not cut out
for living amongst humans.
I don't belong
here.
You doin' okay?
Nanami?
You came for me.
Oh Nanami.
Don't you die here, mister.
You got your whole
life ahead of you!
Who're you?
Where'd Lady Nanami go?
Where am I?
Thank goodness
you're finally awake!
We're outside the wrap party.
I was headin' to get
a drink for the old bag
when I saw you keeled over,
lookin' all green.
I guess ya had a little
trouble holdin your alcohol.
Would ya like some
cold water, hun?
You were with me
this entire time?
Thank you.
I'm sorry!
I still have some
trouble recognizin'
which famous
celebrities are which!
I just moved here
from the country.
I came to the city wantin'
to become an actress,
but this is my first time
goin' to a fancy party.
I'm just so awkward around
all these big stars
that I can't even
think straight.
Everything tonight's
felt like such a blur!
To top things off, I got
to see Kurama in person!
He looked perfect, it's hard
to believe he's even human!
That's because he isn't.
I've been so flustered
that I haven't even had
a normal conversation with
anyone today, 'cept for you.
It's nice to know there's at
least one person in this place
I can talk to.
Thank you for that.
You don't fit in here, either?
You shouldn't force yourself
to be somebody you aren't.
I admit that I still haven't
found my way and ya' know
maybe I never will.
But truth is--
I like this city.
I really do.
I'll work hard and do
my best to make it here.
Listen to me!
Shucks.
Wow.
Shoot, I gotta hustle
back inside to the party!
She told me to get her
a drink and here I am
goin' on long tangents!
I get it now.
Well it was nice meetin' you
and chattin' for a bit.
I have to start
heading home myself.
Oh my!
Thank you for helping me.
Have this, my sacred sake.
Drink it, and it
cleanses the body.
Serve it, and it will
bring good fortune.
It is the sake of gods.
Thank you again for
looking after me tonight.
I've learned this isn't
the right place for me,
and it's not the life I want.
But for others, that
might not be the case.
They don't care what
obstacles get in their way;
they'll go after their
dreams no matter what.
They're stronger
than I thought.
And resilient.
It's truly an inspiration.
This aroma takes me back.
Please, God, help me
become more like them.
Give me their strength, too.
So what did you think,
Master Mizuki?
Your first outing.
Right now I've only
got one thing on my mind.
What's Tomoe gonna do to me
once he finds out I spent all
the offering money on a sticker?
Nanami's awfully
excited this morning!
Seize the day, girl!
Lady Nanami, where could you be
heading so early in the morning?
Oh, I guess I forgot to
tell you guys last night.
Today, Tomoe and I are
going to ride a Ferris wheel!
Exciting, right?
Without a care in the world,
Nanami is focused
on enjoying the day.
Wake up sleepyhead,
the bus is almost here.
What're you doing still in bed?
You can go alone
if you so desire.
But you told me
that you would go!
Hey do you wanna go to
the amusement park and ride
the Ferris wheel this weekend?
She lied.
Geez, you're such a moron!
And after I dressed up
for the occasion!
I'm gonna ransack your room
and find all of
your dirty magazines.
A hair stick?
How pretty.
That's weird.
Why would you have
a woman's hair stick
just lying around in your room?
It is really none
of your business.
Hair stick.
Who does it belong to?
Shall we go to the park now?
And here we are,
at the amusement park.
The second half of this
episode will take place
at everyone's
favorite dating spot!
Finally!
I haven't been here in forever!
Is that the
so-called Ferris wheel?
I do not understand the appeal.
All it does is spin.
So, about that hair stick
that was in your room.
I could spin for hours
on that giant circle!
I say we head over
to it right now?
Why is he acting all strange?
That stick has to
mean something to him.
Otherwise, why have it at all?
I'm going to stop
worrying about it.
I just gotta sit back
and let in the funshine!
There're three things
on today's agenda,
fun at the amusement park,
dinner during sunset,
and the grand finale,
enjoying the night view
from atop the Ferris wheel.
Why?
We could ride the
Ferris wheel right now
and get it out of the way.
Nope!
The Ferris wheel
is meant for night;
it's more romantic that way.
Um, excuse me.
Do you mind if I snap
a quick picture of you?
Also, can I post it to my blog?
Gosh he's hot!
Never mind about that, miss.
Your hat is slightly off-center.
Doesn't he know it's supposed
to be worn like that?
What!
No thank you so
much for fixing it!
How could I be so clumsy?
Thanks again!
I am happy to be
of service to you.
I bet you're "happy to be
of service", you big jerk!
I do not see what
the fuss is about.
So I touched a human woman.
As I have already stated,
all human girls, including you,
are of little interest to me.
Whatever, do what you want.
I couldn't care less
about what you think.
Nothing you say can faze me.
Even if you told me
you were into a human girl
hundreds of years ago.
Aw crap, you idiot!
So much for never
bringing that up to him.
What was that?
What?
I believe I just heard
humans screaming in agony.
Humans screaming?
What is that contraption?
Uh, that's called
a roller coaster.
Only crazy people like
to ride that kind of stuff.
May I direct your attention
to the merry-go-round?
Fascinating!
It looks like fun!
Wouldn't you agree?
Oh my god!
Let me off!
I hate you!
Why did I agree to this?
Open your eyes, Nanami!
Look ahead!
No way!
He's laughing.
I've never seen him
like that before.
I can't believe it!
He's actually happy.
It makes me happy, too!
It's almost as if
we're on a real date.
Nanami.
Your hair is in disarray.
What?
Oh no, please look away!
The wind appears to have
blown it all over the place.
Do you mind if
I fix it for you?
Sit still, please.
Seriously?
How did you even do that?
It took you no time at all, but
you didn't use pins or anything!
I did use a hair stick.
What?
Just one.
And it looks perfect.
I'm in heaven.
Tea and some nuggets, please.
Hey, aren't you the girl
with the boyfriend who
wears a kimono?
Today the park is buzzing
about the cute boy
wearing traditional clothing.
Here's an extra toothpick
so you two can share.
Um, thanks.
But we're actually
not dating or anything.
Ah, really?
That's too bad.
But I am hoping that things
will turn out that way!
Wouldn't that be nice?
One day, I just know
he'll come around.
She stumbled and I
helped her to her feet.
That is all.
And you fondled her hair.
It became disheveled
when she fell down.
So I touched a human woman.
As I have already
stated multiple times.
All human girls, including you,
are of little interest to me.
You're lying.
Don't say it!
You did have feelings
for a human way back when!
What did you say?
You used to love
a woman named Yukiji.
Don't deny it.
I can't stop myself.
For all I know, that
hair stick in your room
was probably hers, too.
What are you going on about?
I know of no such woman.
Wherever did you hear
such far-fetched stories?
Better yet, which roller
coaster should we ride next?
You don't have to talk about
her if you don't want to.
But--
Don't lie to me!
What a jerk!
Playing dumb like that!
If I hadn't seen it for myself,
then I'd believe
every word he said.
But it doesn't really matter.
He loved her long
before I was even born.
So why's he pretending
it didn't happen?
Are there other lies
he's hiding from me, too?
I wonder when he can't
keep throwing me the
"no, I can't love you because
you're human" line anymore.
What other excuses
will he come up with?
Tomoe.
Maybe he got mad and went home.
I wouldn't blame him.
I should probably start
heading back, too.
Maybe I'll be able to
spot him from up there.
The park's so beautiful.
Everything's beautiful at night.
But as pretty as it is,
it's just not the same
when you're alone.
I'm so stupid.
We were supposed to ride
the Ferris wheel together,
but I threw a fit,
like some spoiled brat.
Those lights.
They're from that roller
coaster we rode earlier today.
Why did I have to go
and ruin everything?
Tomoe's hairdo.
It came undone!
I did use a hair stick.
And it looks perfect.
I have finally found you.
Tomoe?
I'm sorry about everything
that happened earlier.
Is this the wheel you
wanted to ride with me?
Um, yes!
You must be happy
you got to ride it.
Yeah.
So then smile.
Like you did earlier.
So, um, this hair stick.
I bought it over yonder.
You did?
I did.
Truthfully, it did not seem
like you would ever use it,
so I put it away.
After all, it is rare
that you put your hair up.
In that moment.
I felt more love for him
than I ever had before.
I hated the Ferris wheel
for continuing to turn.
Tomoe, thank you.
I will never forget this.
The night I realized
he loved me back.
Nothing in the world could make
me happier than I am right now.
Mikage Shrine's worshippers
are dwindling by the day.
Local residents
won't stop gossiping,
calling the place
"spooky" and "beat-up".
Rude.
But our Nanami
won't have any of it!
In fact, she's putting
on a grand festival
to drum up business!
What an entrepreneur!
Next time, "Nanami
Quits Being A God".
Wait, that sounds terrible!