Using the time-wending incense
burner; Nanami arrived in
the past encountering Tomoe,
who had just then stolen
the Dragon King's right eye.
Now, he is standing before her.
Although, she hardly
recognizes this wild fox.
That's it.
That's the Dragon King's eye.
Wait!
Come back!
Tomoe!
He's getting away!
There's no way you'll be able
to catch up to him on foot.
Times likes these must make it
tough to be a land god.
I'm sorry about this!
That's right.
The Tomoe of this time
period hasn't met me yet.
He wouldn't recognize me.
So, do you have any idea
where he's going?
Hm, perhaps he's late to
a party and is bringing
the Dragon King's
eye as a side dish?
Not funny!
We have to get it back!
He'll understand if I explain
the situation to him!
Silly girl.
He won't empathize because
he doesn't know you.
I believe the only
option now is to steal.
Think you can handle it?
You mean break in?
Is that his house?
Looks like it!
I can smell the salt.
You went all the way to
the sea to buy medicine?
Yes.
What I have found
was worth the risk.
Now all you have
to do is take this
and your illness will be cured.
Yukiji.
Get well, live
eternally with me.
That's his voice and his face
and yet I can hardly
recognize him.
He did it for her.
He stole the eye and put his
life at risk for that woman.
She's so beautiful.
Is this the first time
you've felt the pain
of jealousy and envy, Nanami?
You understand me now.
It is too large
to swallow like this.
I will need to find some water.
Such a rare cure must
be consumed properly.
I shall return.
Now is your chance.
She's too weak to fight back.
Go in and take it.
Stop hesitating, Nanami.
If it were up to me,
the task would be completed.
That woman is in your way.
Hang in there!
It'll all be over soon.
Just take this!
Here.
What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
Mizuki?
You traveled all the way here
to find the Dragon King's eye.
Why would you give it away?
She's sick.
Do you realize what you could
be risking if you decide
to choose her life over another?
I wasn't thinking.
I'm here because I wanted
to save Tomoe's life.
Still do.
But there's another person
suffering right in front of me.
I can't stand by and do nothing!
Give it back!
I know that was hard.
Thank you.
But why?
It's okay.
Thank goodness!
Look how quickly
it healed her illness!
That's great.
Let's go.
Wending through time as your
corporal self does not last.
Your time is up.
The solution was never going
to be found in the past.
What I owe now, I have
to pay in the present.
Somehow.
Welcome back!
I have to go!
You shouldn't try
to stand up so quickly.
I imagine you're sore.
Wending through time can be
quite rough on the human body.
So, what do you plan to do now?
That woman I met--Isohime.
Is there any way I could
find her again in the present?
Isohime?
Why would you want to see her?
She said something to me
that I want to ask about.
I'll make you a deal.
Give me the Dragon King's
eye inside you and in return,
I will give you my warm cloak.
She told me that the Dragon
King's eye was inside of me.
Then she asked if I'd be
interested in trading it
for her cloak.
I wonder if that's it.
Could it be the key
to saving Tomoe?
What's going on?
It looks like you're
running some kinda shop
out of this cave.
I'm only here for
a limited time!
How 'bout this fruit?
Feed it to any lady and
she'll do whatever you say!
Won't find one like
it anywhere else.
I'll trade you for that
gold ring on your finger.
Good deal, right?
Dude, what the heck?
Is it high tide?
Uh, maybe we should go back!
I'm not done with you!
You have not changed a bit
in five hundred years.
But thanks to that,
you were easy to track down.
And just who the hell are you?
We need to talk.
I want to make a deal with you.
Really?
And so on and so forth;
and so on and so forth;
What did you just say?
I don't want you to be burdened
with the Dragon King's eye!
Give it to me!
Where is it?
You put it in here?
Well, hold on a sec.
I have to say, you
were a lot different
five hundred years ago.
That's not what I meant!
You told me the Dragon King's
eye was inside of me.
I need you to help me
get it out.
Let's see.
That's interesting.
Something's definitely
swimming around in there.
It looks like the
King's eye except that
it's completely
worn down and tiny.
Are you serious?
Don't let this bod fool ya.
I know what I'm doing.
All right, what are you going to
give me in exchange for this?
Anything you want!
As long as it's
in my power to give!
Really?
Well then--
I want thirty years
of your life!
Take it or leave it!
That's the best deal I've got!
Thirty years is not a
deal; it's a rip-off!
She knows you're desperate so
she's taking advantage of you.
Don't trust her.
And how exactly do you
plan to help her, then?
You don't even know
where the eye is!
Both my eyes have Second Sight!
There's nothing
I can't see through.
Keep out of this, you
pathetic snake-boy has-been.
Okay, let's make a deal!
You can have
thirty years of my life.
There's a girl who
knows how to bargain!
Nanami, don't!
Don't do it.
It'll be okay.
I'm still young, you know.
Not like I'm gonna die
if she takes thirty years.
Don't worry about me.
It's Tomoe who might only have
one more day left to live.
You're so ridiculous.
You are barely capable
of doing anything.
Why are you taking these risks?
You always get in
over your head and
take on more than
you can handle.
I can't put up
with this anymore.
Go ahead and lie down.
Let's begin.
You can give me your
years upon delivery.
Just relax for now.
It'll all be over soon.
Why, thank you, Second Sight.
My my.
It appears that you have
something much more valuable
than years,
Little Miss Land God!
A Dragon King's eye
and a Land God's soul!
Ha!
What a lucky day to be me!
I tried to warn you.
I thought this might happen.
Would it have been so
difficult for you to listen
and trust me to protect you?
Tomoe only has himself
to blame for what happened.
It is not your responsibility
to take on his debt.
Your kindness is relentless.
Nothing I said was
going to stop you.
Familiars at your service are
pointless since your mortal soul
is what leads you
to protect others.
Your heart is what
leads me to serve you.
This is my way.
Of showing how much
I truly respect you.
The cage around my heart
is breaking away.
You just-- but why?
I will continue
to stay by her side.
And then--I'll be able
to be myself again.
Greetings, my new
lady and mistress.
Did you have a nice rest?
Today is the first day
that I, Mizuki,
serve you as your new familiar!
I'll be so useful that I'll blow
Tomoe right out of the water!
Huh?
Wait a second!
What exactly do you mean?
Good news, right?
What happened was--
Not so fast.
You tried to hurt and
deceive my lady and mistress.
It wouldn't be right for me
to let you get away with that,
would it?
Mizuki, stop!
Don't you dare kill her!
Sacred Word Binding.
It ensures absolute obedience.
Sweet paralysis.
What a pleasure being held
under a god's control.
It's euphoric!
Please give me more
commands, Nanami!
Tie me up with your
invisible chain of words!
You're disgusting!
Am I hearing this right?
Did you actually
kiss me in my sleep?
You pervert,
that's sexual assault!
That assessment is
a little over-the-top;
but I am glad you're
adapting to the new changes.
Is this the Dragon King's eye?
It's barely the size
of a pachinko ball.
Who cares what size it is?
It's still the Dragon
King's eye, isn't it?
Let's hurry and
get it back to him!
A deal is a deal, right?
Can we discuss what
happened with Isohime?
Look, I never took anything.
So just take those
and we'll call it even!
All we got were tickets to
the Dragon King's palace.
I still don't think that
you should have let her off
the hook so easily.
I was just worried about
getting her out of here
so you wouldn't kill her.
I assure you, a familiar will
never kill in front of his god.
Surely Tomoe was
the same, right?
He never wanted you
to see his dirty work.
It might have upset you.
Lord Dragon King!
There's trouble headed
right toward us!
Shut up!
Can't you see I'm calculating?
But sir, it's the white lipped
oyster in the banquet hall!
Tomoe?
Good grief.
The sensation of being wrapped
up in flesh brought back
such fond memories.
It's been a long time,
Dragon King, has it not?
You had quite some nerve showing
your face in front of Nanami.
Smart move, as you know I will
not conduct bloody business
in front of my mistress.
Which is why
I decided to change venues.
Wow!
This is amazing!
You really do have to ride on
the back of a turtle to get
to the Dragon King's palace!
Nanami, please.
I told you that window will
let everything through
except for water.
I need you to be
very careful.
Now I can rescue Tomoe.
I'll get to see him
in the present again,
where he remembers me!
Wait.
What's gotten into me?
Mizuki?
Yes?
What's wrong?
Yukiji.
Do you think Tomoe still--.
Do you think he still
has feelings for her?
I'm scared now.
I'm worried about
seeing him again.
All I'm going to
think about is her.
I can't help but compare.
He was so different.
He was sweet to her.
They were passionate.
He clearly loved her.
He won't even touch me.
No!
Shut up!
Now is not the time!
My negative thoughts
are eating me alive!
Why don't we just
forget the trip?
Why would I want to do that?
You don't seem
enthusiastic about it.
In fact, you look
quite miserable.
Hey, would you mind
telling us what's going on?
New passenger boarding
at an unscheduled stop.
Pardon me for
sharing your ride.
One of the dragon folk?
We don't mind at all, welcome.
No!
Not at all!
It's a pleasure.
Nice to meet you!
Oh great!
Why am I the only woman
I know that doesn't
look like a goddess?
I am very curious as to
why a land god would want
to visit a dragon's palace?
Oh, uh.
That's a very good question.
Really weird--my friend
is being held as collateral
so I'm going to go get him.
Oh my, how terrible for you!
I am sure he is looking
forward to seeing you again.
I understand.
You see, I am on my way
to see my beloved husband.
I hope we will both see
our loved ones soon.
Wow!
What beautiful embroidery!
May I ask what that is?
It is called a haori half-coat.
I spent seven days
on the needlework.
In times when I cannot be
with my love, that is how
I remind him of
my eternal feelings.
What a beautiful gift.
I could never make
something like that no matter
how much time I spent.
The half-coat!
Watch out!
But the coat she's
been working on for days
just flew out the window!
We have to go get it!
Please, no.
What?
With that volume of water,
I have no doubt that it has
been carried away by now.
More importantly, I think that
stray current may have been
due to a tremor
coming from the Palace.
I can always make
another half-coat.
Let us head to the
palace immediately.
But you spent
so many days making it.
Yes I did!
And because of that, those days
went by very joyfully indeed.
The memories mean just as much!
I see.
I feel so ashamed.
Until just moments ago, the only
thing I'd been thinking about
was all the ways someone I cared
for didn't return my feelings.
When did I become
so self-centered?
"He doesn't care for me."
"He won't touch me."
Now I think I understand.
No way!
So this is where
the Dragon King lives?
Wow.
I seem to have lost Mizuki
somewhere along the way.
Whoa!
Sounds like someone's
doing construction!
Just as I feared.
Something is
definitely going on.
Lady Kamehime!
Sea Slugs.
What is all the
commotion about?
The fox prisoner suddenly
went on a rampage, sea slug.
The Lord Dragon King is putting
him down in the western palace,
sea slug.
No.
Tomoe!
Very impressive.
You're much more beastly
now than when I saw
you on the beach.
You were right about
the way you look.
Even a thousand year love
would cool if that girl
ever saw you like this.
So then you know Nanami?
She came pestering me,
demanding that I give you back.
She offered to go find
my right eye and return it
in exchange for you.
That is absolute rubbish.
She is the only land god who
is incapable of anything.
That crazy girl is a land god?
I thought that
she was your lover!
She may not look the part,
but she is still the
god of Mikage Shrine.
She is not some woman
to be touched carelessly
with sullied hands.
Tomoe!
I'm so glad to see you!
What?
What is the point of shutting
yourself up in there?
I already know everything!
Come out!
It's too late
to try to deny it!
Fine then.
Well, I went to the past
and met the old you.
I don't care anymore that
you won't open up to me
or if you don't
want to touch me.
That's okay.
Even if you have feelings for
someone else, that's okay.
I've decided I'm not going
to wait for my feelings
to be returned anymore.
You are too close!
It doesn't matter that you
don't see me in that way.
I know someday
you'll change your mind.
Even if you were
to refuse to see me
as anything more than a friend.
Nothing will change the fact
that I have feelings for you.
Ya' know why?
Because it's enough.
Are you ready to go home now?
I don't get it.
Nothing about her
says 'Land God.'
All I can see is a human girl.
It's nonsense.
Um, sir?
Someone is here.
Hello, Darling.
Do you have any explanation
for the unsightly state
of this palace, my love?
I thought you were
visiting your family!
I've missed you, my sweet wife!
Wife?
She's married to him?
You are still toying
with that wild fox
in spite of what happened?
When your eye was stolen,
you promised me you would
never allow another
scar upon your face!
Did you forget
about that, sweetie?
Of course not!
I can explain!
That Land God insisted
on looking for my eye
and returning it to me.
Isn't that right, Land God?
Tell the truth!
Oh right!
I did want to return it!
Here it is!
What the heck?
It's all shriveled up!
Yeah, but if you could
just look past that?
No.
Forget it.
The deal's off.
All right, then.
Why don't we renegotiate
for this beautiful half-coat
I found?
There you are!
You're really offering
me a scrap of cloth?
You think you can do business
with me using a piece of trash?
Oh, no.
I figured you would want
the beautiful gift your wife
spent several days
making for you.
Or not?
Oh well.
Perhaps something
like this isn't equal to
the value of a fox?
You've got a deal!
Mizuki!
So that's where you went!
To go find the half coat!
Please explain to me
why you are here.
Why wouldn't I be here?
I was so worried about
my big brother familiar.
What?
Oh that's right,
he doesn't know.
You and I are going to be taking
care of the shrine together.
What?
I think it's time to go home.
For all three of us!
Let's travel back
several hundred years ago
to when Tomoe became
Mikage's familiar!
Can't wait to see what life
was like for these two.
Next time, "Tomoe
Becomes A Familiar".
What?
There's another story?
And "The God Goes To A Mixer"!
My stars!
I love a double feature!