Does Miyako have...
a boyfriend or what?
Huh?
So, you got a thing for her?
Well, I--
I don't know, man. Maybe.
Uhh.
Can you blame me?
She's a really nice girl.
Isn't she?
Yeah, she's pretty cool.
A boyfriend though.
Wouldn't be surprised
if she had one.
-What you doing with your phone?
-One sec.
There, I just asked her.
Uh-- Dude, what?
That's way too upfront!
You want to know,
so I'm finding out.
Are you sure it isn't weird?
[phone chimes]
Huh?
What the...
He's asking if I'm taken?
Is he interested in me?
That doesn't make sense.
He likes Nayu.
Uhh.
What does this mean?
[phone vibrates]
Uh, she already texted back.
[phone chimes]
[MIYAKO]
"Don't worry about it."
Are you kidding me?
[grunts]
Yes! I'm so gonna
ask her out soon.
And if she says yes,
I'll be back on the upswing.
You're certainly
passionate about this.
Just optimistic.
I'm at rock bottom
'cause of my anime.
So, I've got nowhere else
to go but up.
I understand.
You want a wingman?
[ITSUKI]
Why did I say that?
I don't even know
what a wingman does!
Oh, by the way, Itsuki.
Yeah?
I've been thinking about
throwing a surprise party.
A party for who?
Myaa! Her birthday is
on April 29th,
and that's coming up
a lot sooner than I realized!
[chuckles]
Oh!
And I assume
you want to use my place?
Yup.
A birthday party.
That might be a chance
for Haruto to make his move.
-Let's do it.
-[chuckles]
I'll tell Haruto
and Chihiro too.
Now I just need
to find a gift.
I'm gonna need your advice
for this one. Got it!
Why are you asking me?
[NAYUTA]
I never had any friends
to celebrate birthdays with,
so I wouldn't know what to get.
Oh. Right, I forgot.
But, you know, I didn't
have friends either.
Yeah, but you write rom-coms,
so you should have
some experience.
That's a completely
different beast.
My characters are
so easy to please,
they'd be happy if the hero
gave them anything,
even if it's literally crap.
How should I know
what girls really want?
For the record, I'd be happy
to get literal crap
as long as it's from you.
Whatever, if anyone
gives you crap
as a gift,
that means they hate you.
[NAYUTA]
You wouldn't be like "Whoa,
"she's happy with me
giving her crap?
She must really love me!"?
[giggles]
-Admit it, you would be.
-No!
Okay, well, what if she was
a little sister?
How dare you! I would
never give a little sister crap!
[sighs]
Now if a little sister
gifted me crap,
that's different.
Why the hell
are we talking about crap
when we're trying
to eat brown food?
Probably because
you brought it up?
Sorry about that.
-[typing]
-[sighs]
What to get, what to get.
Thinkin' hard over there?
Oh, yeah!
I want to get her something
that she'll love!
You really do care
for Miyako, don't you?
[chuckles]
Well, yeah, I love her.
I've been meaning to ask you
about that, actually.
Is there a reason
you're so clingy with her?
Myaa's just a sweet girl.
She lets me rely on her
and always looks out for me.
And she's the kind of person
who'll cry
or get angry for my sake.
She's like an older sister
that way.
She's being such
a little sister right now!
You okay?
Uh? Yeah, I'm fine!
Now what were we talking about?
Right, a present.
Uhh.
[ITSUKI]
Hmm.
She has lots of friends
buying her presents.
Maybe get her something
they won't think of.
Like her favorite
author's autograph?
That's a good idea!
Do you happen to know
who that is?
Maybe I know them!
Sorry, no clue.
Hmm. Not to worry.
This is what
we've got technology for.
[phone chimes]
Hmm?
Favorite author?
Umm.
It's a little awkward getting
this from an author friend.
But I guess it has to be him,
even though
I can't always keep up
with everything in his plots.
[NAYUTA]
Hmm.
I got a response, and apparently
her favorite author is you.
What?
Oh. So, she's a fan
of mine, huh?
What was she doing
hiding it this whole time?
[chuckles]
She said that's only
if she had to choose.
What's wrong, Kanikou?
Are you jealous?
No, I'm not. I'm far from it.
I'm sure she likes
your stuff just fine.
Now, down to business.
This autograph isn't about
to write itself!
Hey, everybody.
-[popping]
-[screams]
[ALL]
Happy birthday!
I bet you assumed
we all forgot, huh, Myaa?
So did we surprise you?
Yeah. Very much so.
Can't ask for
a better outcome than that!
[MIYAKO]
Thanks, Nayu.
[NAYUTA crying]
[MIYAKO]
Uh! Is something wrong?
Oh, no, there's nothing
wrong at all!
Happy birthday, Miyako.
Come check out all the food!
[MIYAKO] Did you make
all of this, Chihiro?
[CHIHIRO chuckles]
Yeah.
Wow.
You're surprisingly good
at girly stuff.
What do you mean?
I'm not girly at all!
[NAYUTA]
And this one's from me!
[MIYAKO]
Thank you!
Oh. Should I open it?
Sure.
[MIYAKO]
Huh?
It's an SD card?
What's on it?
Oh, just a novel.
Wait, really?
Duh! And you're
the main character!
-I wrote it especially for you.
-Huh?
No way!
You wrote a story
where I'm the main character?
Better keep that away
from our editors.
They'd do anything to get it.
When you're done,
I have to read it!
That's out of the question.
I wrote that story for her eyes
and her eyes alone.
[grunts]
Thanks a lot, Nayu.
I'm really excited to read it.
Great!
[giggles]
By the way, Myaa.
I gotta ask.
How does it feel
to be 21 now?
How does it feel?
Let me think.
I thought I'd feel more grown up
by 21, but I don't.
You know what I mean?
-Ah, right!
-[sighs] I totally do.
I felt the exact same way
back when I was your age.
Yeah, me, too.
I'm surprised to hear that
from you, Fuwa.
Well, I still read books
and play games every day.
It doesn't feel
all that different
from when I was in school.
Sure, but you're not
in school anymore.
You and Itsuki are independent,
working adults.
Compared to you,
I'm still far behind.
You okay?
You know, when I was younger,
I thought
being this age meant you were
just automatically mature.
Like I'd already have
a goal for my future.
And I'd be working hard
towards it.
And... I'd be in love,
living happily ever after.
What do you mean?
You're a sophisticated woman
who's had plenty
of relationships!
I'm sorry, but that was a lie.
What?
What I said about
my past relationships.
If I'm being honest, I've never
been on a real date before.
Huh?
[MIYAKO]
The truth is...
I'm actually not this mature,
experienced woman
that you want me to be.
Oh, Myaa.
I'm sorry
that I lied to you.
Do you hate me now?
Mmm, no! of course not.
I could never hate you!
Nayu!
I don't love you
because of your experience
or because you're mature,
even though I still believe
that you are.
It's because
you're a good person.
[sniffles]
Nayu.
Whether you've been
with ten guys or zero,
you'll always be
my deeply beloved big sister.
Nayu. Nayu!
[sobbing]
Oh, you!
You're such a little sweetheart!
And I love you too!
[sobbing continues]
I could almost kiss you!
Hey, you can if you want.
What?
I'm saying I wouldn't mind
if you kissed me.
It wouldn't be that big a deal.
Well, I won't.
But only because
your lips belong to Itsuki.
[giggles]
That's a good reason.
And no one thought to ask
my opinion about this?
[exhales]
Huh?
Hmm.
Hmm?
[touchpad clicking]
[heroic music playing]
[heroic music continues]
I love you...
Princess.
And I you, Ikki.
Whoa, wait,
this is a dirty novel!
Not to mention
the knight's appearance
is clearly just Itsuki!
[groans]
Huh?
[heroic music continues]
[moans loudly]
[MIYAKO]
Universe!
I'm blown away.
It's not entirely fantasy
or smut
but sort of a mythology.
Either way, I couldn't stop
reading it for a second.
Uh...
[birds chirping]
Nayu really is amazing.
Isn't she?
I thought I'd feel more grown up
by 21, but I don't.
Could I ever become like them?
[ITSUKI typing]
-Hey.
-[ITSUKI] Hmm?
Do you remember
a couple weeks ago
when you said
you'd help me with something?
[ITSUKI]
Oh, you mean Miyako?
Uh-huh. That.
[ITSUKI]
Yeah, what about it?
I was kinda counting
on you, wingman.
[ITSUKI]
What?
You know,
at the birthday party?
I thought you might try
and find some way
to nonchalantly help
a brother out.
[typing stops]
[ITSUKI]
I forgot.
[groans]
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Even Nayu did better than me.
Her and Miyako almost made out.
Not that I would have complained
if I actually got to see that.
[ITSUKI]
Well, tell you what.
I'll help you out
next time for sure.
Cool. Counting on you, buddy.
[ITSUKI]
Yup. On that subject...
how exactly do you
want me to help?
Just so I'm clear.
What? I don't know.
I figured you'd come up
with something, Captain Rom-Com.
I swear, none of you know
what a romantic comedy is.
[exhales deeply]
How about this?
Let's go to an amusement park.
Okay, why there?
The volume I'm on has a scene
that takes place at one,
so I wanna go for research.
We can invite Miyako and Kanikou
and make it a group thing.
Oh, I get you! You're settin' up
a double date for us.
-Nice!
-It's not a date, dude!
I-- I'm just trying to write
a better story here.
[PEOPLE chattering]
[groans]
So busy.
It's Golden Week.
What do you expect?
I'm so stupid!
How did I forget that?
-Don't worry, I did too.
-It happens.
When you make your own hours,
the days blend together.
I'll never get you writers.
[exclaims excitedly]
You sure look excited.
I'm super excited!
I haven't been
to a place like this
since I was a little kid!
You haven't? Really?
Then why don't you look around
and pick
what we're all gonna do first?
Uh... always the generous one?
Let's see.
"High speeds exceeding
300 kilometers per hour.
A blood-pumping race
filled with spills and thrills."
[grunts]
Are we sure we want to go
on this one first, Kanikou?
What? Don't tell me you can't
handle a little thrill ride.
It's not that. I've just
never been on one before.
I was little when my family
took me to one of these places.
Oh, you're just
like me, then! Ha!
Our first time will be together!
[ITSUKI]
I don't know if we're talking
about the same thing here!
But wouldn't it be a lot better
if we started on a calmer ride?
You are not winning
this fight, man.
I don't like these rides
very much, either.
But she wants to ride it,
so here I am.
-[NAYUTA laughing]
-[groans]
Here we go!
Isn't this exciting?
I've made peace with my death.
Let's do this.
I'm getting butterflies
in my stomach.
Yeah, I hear you. I've had
that feeling all day long.
[steady beeping]
[NAYUTA]
Oh!
Wasn't that so much fun?
It went in circles
and then went whoosh
and then sped up
and went bwam
and then dropped us!
Can you tell I loved it?
Hell, yeah!
I especially liked that part
where it rattled a ton,
then went bam
and flew off!
It was, like,
the best thing ever!
[NAYUTA chuckles]
Yeah, it was
pretty damn intense.
Sure was. I might have
thrown up in my mouth a little.
Okay, which ride
should we go on next?
-There's lots to choose from!
-Doesn't matter!
We'll ride 'em all eventually,
so who cares?
All right! That's what
I like to hear!
You've joined
the thrill-seeking dark side!
What's wrong, Haruto?
The lines are only
getting longer.
Wait. Why don't we
take it easy after that one?
Yeah. I'd appreciate that.
All right, fine, you two.
Since both of you insist,
we can go on a calmer one next.
[BOTH laughing]
-[MIYAKO screaming]
-[HARUTO whimpering]
Think you can handle it?
For you, I'd handle
just about anything.
Miyako, you doin' okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine. Really.
Just a little bit tired.
Hey, you're not the only one.
Uh, wanna take
a quick break, then?
[NAYUTA] You think this one
will live up to the hype?
[ITSUKI]
Hopefully.
[HARUTO]
Here you go.
Uh! Awesome. Thanks so much!
Uh! Huh?
Ah! I, uh, take it this isn't
what you normally do
on your days off.
So what do you do?
Hmm?
I usually go shopping
or to karaoke with some friends.
That sounds fun.
And what about you?
What do you do?
I'm usually holed up
in my room
playing video games
or reading books.
Oh, right, you mentioned that.
-Still, I'm pretty surprised.
-Uh--
I always thought
you were the kind of guy
who goes out
every chance he gets.
Man, that couldn't be
further from the truth.
I've always been more
the indoor type.
You know what?
I have been staying in
and reading more often lately.
Ever since I met Itsuki.
Yeah?
Oh, that reminds me,
have you gotten around
to reading the story
that Nayu wrote?
Yeah, I have.
How was it?
It was great.
But more than anything,
it made me realize just
how good a writer Nayu is.
It almost feels wrong
to be hanging out
with her all the time now.
Wrong like how?
Maybe...
I feel like
she's wasting her time
with someone like me.
I don't know.
Or like
we don't really match up.
[HARUTO chuckles]
I think I know how you feel.
And take it from me,
you shouldn't worry
too much about it.
What makes you say that?
In my line of work,
I'm surrounded by all brands
of genius day in and day out.
If I kept worrying about how
I don't fit in, I'd go crazy.
That's why
I don't think about it.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Uh-- Yeah.
[sighs]
Now that we've gone
on all the rides...
Let's bring the day full circle
and go on the first one again!
Yeah, that'd be awesome!
[whimpers]
Sorry, but I still have
the taste of vomit in my mouth.
I'll pass too.
But you go have fun without us.
You're so hopeless.
Well, let's go, Kanikou.
Yeah!
Uh--
We'll be back in a bit, Myaa!
Cool. We'll be right here.
-Hey, stop pulling my arm!
-[NAYUTA giggles]
[NAYUTA]
I'm so excited!
[ITSUKI]
I know, I know.
[NAYUTA]
That part where it rattles
-then flies off is the best!
-[MIYAKO] Honestly,
they were made for each other.
Yeah.
They should
just go out already.
[HARUTO]
So that's how it is.
I had so much fun!
When are we going again?
Not on a holiday.
[chuckles]
So, you make any progress?
Hmm?
Haruto?
Sorry.
Nothing really happened.
Aww, man. You coward.
[HARUTO chuckles]
It's all right.
I'll just keep
doing things my way.
[wind whooshing]
So, uh, no need
to help anymore.
Huh?
Oh. Okay.
Yeah.
'Cause that wouldn't be fair
to anyone, would it?
Hmm?
Don't worry. It's nothing.
[PEOPLE chattering]
Hmm.
So, how is it?
[exhales]
[laughs]
I'll have to get
the original creator's
opinion on it.