-[ITSUKI chuckling]
-[TOKI snorts]
[TOKI]
Here’s the manuscript
for chapter one of Maho
Academy’s manga.
Whoa!
You’re very excited.
[ITSUKI]
Of course I am!
I’m lucky enough to have Kaiko,
who’s not only
an amazing manga artist,
but completely gets my work!
I’m so pumped to see
how it turned out
I can barely contain myself!
It’s beautiful!
Her art is as great
as I remember!
Way to go, Kaiko!
This is exactly what I wanted!
This bodes well
for the risqué scenes.
[chuckling]
You mean like the one early on,
where Sieg sees
Hilde completely naked?
Hell yeah!
I bet she drew the nudity
in perfect detail!
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Mmm.
[groans]
[grunts]
[yelling]
What is this blasphemy?
Why is she--
Why the hell is Hilde
not completely naked?
Trust me, I was shocked
when I noticed it, too.
But then I learned something.
Our artist, Mikuniyama,
has a huge underwear fetish.
[gasps]
[BOTH chuckle nervously]
[ITSUKI growls]
[whimpers]
[ITSUKI]
So...
If you have an explanation
for why Hilde isn’t naked,
now would the time to speak up.
[KAIKO] Your editor already
told you, didn’t he?
It’s because I--
I truly love underwear!
So I drew some!
"So I drew some!".
Gimme a break!
I thought you understood
my work.
I thought you loved it!
How could you taint it this way?
Please, don’t get me wrong.
I do love your work,
and I appreciate it, too.
-Go on.
-However...
I’ve always felt
there was a very clear
and unfortunate flaw
in your stories!
Here we go.
[KAIKO]
Yes.
Why do you immediately strip
the clothes
off your otherwise perfect
little sister characters?
If you truly loved them,
you’d dress them in
high-quality underwear
worthy of a girlfriend!
[scoffs] So naïve.
A true little sister connoisseur
would want to see it all!
Every last detail.
Implying that a filthy piece
of cloth
should hinder my view of
one inch of that holy body
is outrageous!
All little sisters
are most beautiful
when they are
in their natural state.
Clothing is the one thing that
separates us from wild animals!
And we first become truly human
when we are blessed
with underwear.
Beautiful beings need
beautiful underwear.
That’s the core
principle of man’s
never-ending pursuit
of elegance!
Ridiculous!
Truly enchanting creatures are
perfect without modifications!
Nudity is the ultimate
form of fashion!
If clothing defines
our humanity,
then little sisters
are the perfect animal!
Nudity is not fashion!
To think a monkey that can’t
understand
the allure of underwear
has the nerve to tell me,
a girl from Gunma,
what fashion is.
I’ll have you know that I was
born into a family
that has been farming silk
since the Edo period.
I think I know
what I’m talking about.
What a coincidence.
I didn’t want to brag,
but my grandfather’s family
made a fortune
breeding koi in Gifu
and he was a millionaire.
So I’ve been surrounded by
beauty since I was born as well.
And I think I know
what I’m talking about.
Just as koi are beautiful
as they swim bare,
little sisters are most
beautiful when they are naked.
[KAIKO chuckles derisively]
Gifu? You’re from there?
Well, it’s no wonder you have
the value set of a monkey.
[ITSUKI scoffs]
Gunma?
Well if you were raised there,
I guess I can see why
you’d treat underwear
with such reverence.
You must have been dressed up
in fancy clothes
from the second
you left the womb.
[KAIKO grunts]
[ITSUKI growls]
Can we get back
to the problem at hand?
[BOTH]
This is the problem!
Okay,
but think about it.
Given the quality
of Mikuniyama’s art,
the readers will probably be
satisfied even without nudity.
[ITSUKI]
Don’t be stupid!
I don’t write nude scenes
into my stories
because I want to
make my readers happy!
The reason I write nude scenes
into my stories
is because I want
to make myself happy!
You could at least pretend
to be ashamed.
Then we have something
in common.
I don’t draw underwear
for my readers as well!
I do it because I have
a burning desire
to see adorable
little sisters
wearing the correct
undergarments!
What do we do?
These two are nuts.
-[ITSUKI] Shut up. Huh?
-[doorbell chimes]
Hey man!
Busy?
Yes, I happen to be
in a meeting right now.
[SETSUNA] Well, somebody doesn’t
sound happy. What’s wrong?
Let’s just say
my manga artist and I
aren’t exactly
seeing eye to eye.
Oh.
You mean Mahou Academy?
Would you mind if I came inside
to say hi?
I guess.
Hello!
I’m the illustrator Puriketsu.
Wait.
You’re the Puriketsu?
It’s an honor to meet you!
I’m a new manga artist.
My name is Kaiko Mikuniyama.
It’s a pleasure!
[gasps]
Is this the manga manuscript?
Oh wow!
You’re really good, aren’t you?
Hold on.
Shouldn’t she be--
Naked!
And yet this woman dared
to draw panties and a bra
over Hilde’s pure
erogenous zones!
[SETSUNA]
Whoa!
What in the hell
were you thinking?
Putting panties on a girl
who’s supposed to be naked?
Just what kind of monster
are you?
No. You too, Puriketsu?
I can’t believe the influence
of nude supremacy
has been able
to spread itself this far.
[SETSUNA]
This is unbelievable!
I can sort of understand
the bra,
but she should not
be wearing panties!
[ITSUKI]
What are talking about?
I don’t want a single thread
on her body!
She’s supposed to be
completely nude!
[KAIKO] I can’t believe
you’d have her in just a bra!
That’s ridiculous!
You’re a heathen, Puriketsu!
You know what?
If she’s facing forward,
then whatever, panties are fine.
But if we’re talkin’
a full-on ass shot,
I want 'em on the ground
where they belong!
How can you expect me to draw
something so clearly unnatural?
Bras and panties
are worn as a set!
That’s one issue
I won’t budge on.
Itsuki, man!
There’s no way
we can leave Mahou Academy
in the hands
of someone like this!
[growling] Damn it.
Here’s the problem.
I want to say
that I agree, but...
other than this scene,
these illustrations are
a absolutely perfect adaptation.
[growls]
You have so much talent.
Why did you have to go and be an
underwear-obsessed weirdo, too?
And what about you?
How did you end up
as a disgusting nude-lover?
I’d expect better from someone
who understands little sisters.
That settles it, I’ll take over!
[ALL]
Huh?
I’m gonna draw the Mahou Academy
manga myself!
[TOKUYAMA]
Are you kidding me?
[TOKI]
You can’t just do that!
[ITSUKI] Do you even know
how to put together a manga?
I can probably manage it.
I’m sorry,
but that’s not happening.
This is my job and I’ll see it
through to the end!
Okay then.
Let’s compete.
Winner draws the manga.
I may respect you, but I’m not
going to lose to you.
I swear.
Uh, all right.
We will now begin the manga
competition
between Puriketsu
and Mikuniyama.
I guess.
The two of you will draw
that scene with Hilde
we were talkin’ about,
and the three of us will judge.
Be prepared, because I’m not
planning to go easy on you.
I won’t either, I’m gonna
show you how it’s done.
What are your thoughts,
Tokuyama?
Well, if I had to say,
as an experienced manga editor,
I know how beneficial
it would be
to have Puriketsu’s name
attached to this product.
And since the character is nude
in the original story,
I do feel as though she should
be nude in the manga, as well.
Well there you have it.
It seems the judges feel
that Puriketsu
has a clear advantage
in today’s competition.
Why are you acting like
we have an audience?
Anyway, are the two of you
ready to start yet?
-[KAIKO] No, one moment, please!
-Huh?
[MEN gasp]
♪
[TOKI gasps]
You gotta be kidding.
Are those panties?
Yes. That they are.
[cooing]
Uh, hold on,
do you mean to tell me
you’ve had panties on your head
this whole time?
God damn right I have.
[ITSUKI]
You’re so weird!
Maybe, but using panties
as a ribbon is my right,
isn’t it, Hashima?
[ITSUKI]
Uhh.
I mean, it’s your property.
But still, why are you
pulling them out now?
Kaiko Mikuniyama.
Preparing for battle!
[MEN]
What?!
Now, let us begin
this war of art!
Woah whoa whoa whoa whoa!
What the hell are you doing
with those on your face?
This is my formal uniform
that I use when I draw manga.
[ITSUKI]
Formal uniform?
I guess there are authors who
change clothes when they work.
Kanikou gets naked
when she writes.
So putting panties on your face
for your craft,
it’s, uh...
I guess it’s, uh...
It's...
Fine!
All right.
For real this time!
Let the manga battle begin!
-Yes, sir!
-Let’s go!
♪
[BOTH yelling]
[growling]
I’m finished!
The same goes for me!
Okay.
Let’s start with
Setsuna’s, then.
[ALL gasp]
-[SETSUNA chuckles]
-[MEN gasp]
Whoa!
[sighs]
[ITSUKI] Those nudes are
freakin’ awesome, man.
[SETSUNA chuckles]
And now on to Kaiko’s.
Huh?
What the hell’s going on!
There’s even less showing
than before!
[growling]
Although...
[ALL gasping]
[KAIKO] Well?
Have any comments?
Do you like my manga?
[TOKI]
Mm-hmm.
[ITSUKI]
It’s unanimous.
All three judges cast
their vote for Mikuniyama.
[applause]
[chuckles softly]
I guess I still have a ways
to go, huh?
Sorry, man.
I really do think
your artwork is fantastic.
But it felt like it was
a drawing not a manga.
Whereas Mikuniyama found
the story
to be told in the way
Hilde took off her underwear.
Even I, a die-hard
nude supremacist
couldn’t peel my eyes
away from that.
Well you’re the winner
and you know what that means.
I’m glad to be working with you
on Mahou Academy.
Yes!
The same to you!
Thank you for having me,
Hashima.
♪
[ITSUKI]
So frilly.
[NAYUTA gasps]
[yelps]
What the hell, Kaniko?
[NAYUTA] Why are you browsing
an underwear site?
Not that it’s your business,
but I was researching
material for my book.
Since when has underwear
played a big enough part
in your novels to research?
I’d understand if you were
gonna describe them,
but why would you bother?
You always have them taken off
by the next sentence anyway.
Yeah.
That is how I would have
handled it in the past.
But from now on I’m writing
in-depth scenes
depicting girls in underwear.
Wait what?
Where did this come from?
The artist doing my manga,
Mikuniyama.
[sighs]
She made me realize just how
wonderful underwear can be.
♪
Mikuniyama, huh?
She’s messed with your head.
I knew she couldn’t be trusted.
[whimpers]
Nayuta Kani.
I already know your name,
so don’t bother.
In case you didn’t know,
I’m Itsuki’s wife.
Hey, now.
You really shouldn’t lie
to someone you just met.
[growls]
Fine. I’m his future wife.
Uh, okay.
Oh, and I’m Miyako Shirakawa.
I’m Itsuki and Nayu’s friend.
I was just asked to tag along,
so pretend I’m not even here.
Um, so what’s this about?
You’re Gift Pub’s
most popular author.
What do you want with me?
All right, let’s get
straight to the point.
You’re luring Itsuki down
the wrong path
and I want you to stop it.
What exactly do you mean by,
"Wrong path?"
Well, have you not made changes
while adapting Itsuki’s story?
Uh, yes.
I made some changes.
What kind of changes?
I’m glad you asked.
This woman had the nerve
to put underwear
on the main heroine
in her nude scene!
Oh.
[NAYUTA] It doesn’t sound like
you’re taking this seriously!
Well, it doesn’t sound
like that big a deal.
Oh, no.
What happened to you Myaa?
You used to love nudity
as much as me.
When did I ever say
that I loved nudity?
[NAYUTA]
What do you mean?
We’ve been naked together
in the ocean and this very room!
[MIYAKO]
Well, yeah, but...
[NAYUTA] We even got naked
in the middle of the street
and got arrested!
[MIYAKO] No we didn’t,
that was in a game!
Is this some sort of
exhibitionist thing, or what?
[MIYAKO] No no no no!
You’ve got the wrong idea!
I swear, I’m not
some perverted nudist!
That can’t be true.
I don’t believe this!
[scoffs]
Well, well, well, it seems
as though you’re the only one
with these wicked thoughts.
[NAYUTA groans]
[KAIKO] Underwear is the
ultimate form of beauty!
Whether they’re in the shower,
eating their breakfast,
or listening intently
to a lecture,
beautiful girls need only dress
themselves in underwear.
Oh great, so you’re
a weirdo, too!
[KAIKO]
Hmm?
Yes, too weird to leave
with the responsibility
of Mahou Academy!
Incorrect.
There is undeniably no one
out there
who can better express that
story in manga form than I.
[gasps] You’re full of it!
That story’s important to me.
I’m sure I can express it
better than you can!
[KAIKO] Is that so?
Care to bet?
[NAYUTA]
Bring it on.
[groaning]
[KAIKO giggles]
Nayu.
You’re really not very good
at drawing.
[NAYUTA moaning]
[KAIKO]
That makes me the winner.
Uhh, don’t get ahead
of yourself.
That was just
the practice round!
Let’s throw down
for real this time!
[groans]
Come on, don’t be like that.
I don’t know anything
about manga
and even I can
tell hers is amazing.
I don’t care how good she is!
No one has the right to cover up
what is supposed to be nudity!
Not to mention, this problem
directly affects my future!
Now you’re just overreacting.
Um, would you mind explaining
how my manga
supposedly affects your future?
I certainly don’t mind.
So you know how I said
I’m going to marry Itsuki?
Yeah?
[NAYUTA[ Well, I’m basically
naked at home all the time!
My dream is to live a married
life overflowing with love
where Itsuki can’t keep
his hands off of me
because he’s always
subjected to my naked body!
[BOTH] Then maybe you
should get a new dream!
No chance.
And that’s why I don’t want
Itsuki to start
liking non-nudity!
What if he stops
lusting after me?
My perfect life will be ruined!
Then you could just
put on some lingerie.
Still, I have no plans to remove
the underwear from my manga.
Fine!
You leave me no choice!
Woah!
What do you think you’re doing!
I’m going to show you
the glory that is nudity!
[NAYUTA grunts]
What is this?
I’ll show you what bare,
naked boobs feel like!
I-I already know what they
feel like, I have my own!
Oh, yeah? Are you sure?
-[KAIKO gasps]
-[NAYUTA] Mikuniyama,
don’t tell me.
Could it be that you’ve
never played
with another
woman’s breasts?
So what if is true?
Plenty of girls
haven't you know!
-[NAYUTA sighs]
-[KAIKO yelps]
[NAYUTA] I only recently learned
of this myself,
but fondling another girl’s
boobs is completely different
from exploring your own.
-[KAIKO] What?
-Oh, you sweet, young thing.
[yelps] What was that?
[NAYUTA[ You do draw underwear
incredibly well.
Oh, thanks, but can you
move your hand?
[NAYUTA] If you would only use
your talent to draw nudes
instead, Itsuki’s fans
could be fully satisfied.
Please stop!
But you insist on drawing girls
covered up.
And that's a shame!
I’m not telling you that you
can’t ever draw underwear.
But you can draw characters
naked sometimes, can’t you?
[screams]
Unless of course,
you don't know how
to draw a naked female body.
Perhaps because you’ve
never felt a woman's curves
up close and personal before?
Never gotten yourself a handful?
I can draw the naked female
form no problem.
Of course, I can’t draw it
as well as I can draw
underwear, but even so.
[NAYUTA]
Are you sure you aren’t just
running away from nudity?
Hiding your inability
by embracing underwear?
[KAIKO gasps]
[KAIKO]
Yes, I am sure!
And I’ll prove it to you, too.
I love underwear!
It’s not that I’m running away
from being naked.
I chose underwear, despite being
well-educated in women’s bodies!
Allow me to demonstrate!
[yelps]
[NAYUTA moaning]
Seems you were right.
This is indeed different
from fondling my own breasts.
Hold on a second, I’m confused,
how can this be?
How could someone like you,
who despises nudity,
be so good
at fondling someone’s boobs?
I’m a manga artist.
I’m very good with my hands.
[NAYUTA]
Then manga artists are amazing.
Damn right.
[NAYUTA]
This is embarrassing.
Don’t look.
[KAIKO]
That’s not going to happen,
I want to observe.
And learn every last detail
of your body.
[NAYUTA moaning]
[KAIKO] You’re turning me
into a nude-believer.
But I have to go deeper.
If I want to truly understand,
I need to dive in head first!
[BOTH moan]
I- I’m sensitive.
I'll analyze your body.
Every curve, every pore,
every inch and fold!
[orgasmic moaning]
[NAYUTA whimpering]
It turns out you were right
from the start.
Nakedness is a theme that
is well worth exploring.
Yay.
Glad to hear it.
You’ll be happy to know
I want to try drawing Hilde
without underwear, now.
Hell yeah!
Awesome!
I did it, Itsuki.
[KAIKO] But I’m afraid
there’s one problem.
[NAYUTA]
Hmm?
I’m only familiar
with two bodies.
Just two sets of boobs
to reference.
But Hilde’s chest is larger
than both of ours.
[chuckles]
That’s not a problem.
We have the perfect model
for Hilde’s boobs
right here in this room!
[KAIKO grunts appreciatively]
[KAIKO] Wow, you’re right,
I hadn’t even noticed!
Wait.
Are you talking about me?
Come on Myaa,
you know the drill.
Take it off already!
No! I’m not some nudity-loving
weirdo like the two of you!
Please, Shirakawa?
For art?
It would really help me out!
My manga will be so much better!
I already said no!
I’m not getting naked
under any circumstances!
[moans]
I have such a weird life.
Seriously.
[ITSUKI] And this
is the final manuscript
of Mahou Academy’s manga,
chapter one.
Wow!
[HARUTO]
Wow, it turned out great, man!
I still can’t believe
your series
is being turned into a manga.
That’s so cool!
[ITSUKI]
Yeah!
The details on her underwear
are incredible.
Yeah.
Very provocative.
Huh?
[gasps]
This two-page nude spread
is magnificent!
Dude! Check out
the shading on her boobs!
It’s flawless!
This is just how I envisioned
her in my head!
This is bound to
please everyone.
Both die-hard nudists
and underwear fans.
I’m so thankful.
[ALL laughing]