[GIRL]
Wakey-wakey.
Rise and shine!
That's my big bro.
Good morning!
Hey, Alice. Morning.
[BOY]
This is my little sister Alice.
She may not look it,
but she'll be turning
fourteen this year.
Well, this won't do.
You're still so sweepy!
Guess I'll just have to do
something to wake you up.
Normally I'd want to keep going,
but today's special.
'Cause I made breakfast
and set the table all by myself!
So, hurry your butt downstairs
before it gets cold!
I'll be right there.
[ALICE giggling]
[BOY] I washed my face
in the bathwater
that my sister just used
and wiped it dry with her bra.
-Then headed for the kitchen.
-Uh...
There, I found Yoshiko,
who should have died yesterday.
I was very surprised.
Well, what are you waiting for?
I made it just for you
so dig in!
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Laid before me was an omelet
made from Alice's eggs
and a cup of Alice's milk.
So creamy and rich.
The taste of my little sister
spread throughout my mouth.
Her newly hatched eggs
and freshly squeezed milk
tasted delicious!
You silly-head.
You've got some ketchup
on the corner of your mouth.
What am I gonna do with you?
[BOY] Alice reached through
a portal to a parallel world,
pulled out
some just-worn panties,
and wiped my mouth with them.
My little sister's hot,
fresh-off-the-crotch panties
tasted so good!
The alluring aroma
and tender taste
of her succulent juices
swirled around in my head!
This was enlightenment!
The hell is this?
Easy there!
Where'd that come from, man?
Oh, don't you give me that.
You moron!
This world is a mess.
I'm at a loss for words!
At a loss for words, huh?
I take it you've been moved
by my masterpiece?
You are unbelievably stupid.
[TOKI] All right, just in case
I'm misunderstanding somehow,
this is supposed to be
your manuscript
for the second chapter
of "The Scarlet Jager," right?
That's correct, sir.
That's funny.
According to
the chapter synopsis,
in the opening
of chapter two,
the protagonist is shocked
when the heroine
who died protecting him
from a demon's attack
at the end of chapter one
is having breakfast at his house
the next morning,
like nothing ever happened.
And? What's your point?
That's what I wrote about.
Are we talking about
the same thing?
The protagonist clearly says
he was surprised.
And why was he surprised?
'Cause what's-her-face
was there.
It's Yoshiko!
How can you forget the name
of the main heroine?
But I guess that plotline
is in here,
even if it feels
totally out of place.
[ITSUKI]
Good grief.
What am I going to do
with an editor like you?
Oh, you are not about
to blame this on me.
[exasperated sigh]
Anyway, that's not even
the biggest problem here.
What is?
Who the hell is this new
Alice character
that's in every scene?
I've never once been told
about this girl!
She's the dude's little sis.
If you'd paid attention
to his character bio
that I so painstakingly wrote,
you'd know that.
[TOKI]
It was a single sentence!
I assumed she'd just be
a background character
but you made her a freak!
If by freak
you mean freakishly cute,
then you've totally nailed it!
[TOKI]
No, you dumbass!
Not only is she naked
all the time,
which is already
a big enough offense,
but she's got ridiculous powers
that only exist to encourage
her big brother's
deranged fetish!
I mean, the guy wiped his face
with his sister's bra
and then ate
her dirty underwear!
Come on, man!
-He's just...
-Mm-hmm.
"Disgusting" isn't enough,
but there's no better word!
Let me just confirm
that you didn't
accidentally type "panties"
instead of some kind of food.
[ITSUKI ] I'm insulted.
I'm a professional.
I'd never make such
a stupid mistake like that.
So, "Alice's milk"
wasn't a mistake?
Of course not.
It's simply milk from her boobs.
Delicious, rich,
creamy boob milk
How about Alice's eggs?
Delicious eggs that Alice laid.
I told you, I wouldn't make
a mistake like that.
[inhales sharply]
Denied.
-Huh?
-Denied!
We could never publish this!
Settle down.
I admit that I may have gone
just a teensy bit too far
with the whole milk
and eggs thing.
But the story's
about psychic powers.
Shouldn't I be able
to include some things
that are a little unorthodox?
A little... unorthodox?
Yeah, it happens all the time.
Like when the hero's parents
turn out to be
some legendary adventurer.
Or they're the heir
of some ancient martial art,
and only they have
the skills--
What is wrong with you?
How does a world where people
lay eggs and eat panties
compare to a battle story
with cliche plot points?
Uh...
Okay, but washing your face
with the bathwater
your sister just used is normal.
So, can we keep that?
Everyone does it.
Like hell everyone does it!
You friggin'
sister-complex freak!
I'm serious.
I'm rejecting that manuscript.
[groans]
I don't mind you working
on a new project,
but you better
still be progressing
with volume five
of "Mahou Academy."
The deadline's at the end
of the month.
Yeah. I got it covered.
Why do I feel like
you're lying to me?
I don't know, but I'm not!
I'll get it done.
[sighs]
Honestly, his obsession
with little sisters
is always a problem.
Hello, Toki.
How are you?
Oh.
[TOKI]
Hey, Chihiro. I'm good.
Here for a meeting
with my brother?
Yeah, we just
finished up, actually.
That looks heavy.
-You pick up stuff for dinner?
-Yeah.
Bro's got guests coming over,
so I bought extra.
[chuckles]
You seem like
a pretty reliable
younger brother, kid.
Well, I guess.
Oh.
Thank you for always keeping
my brother on track.
I really appreciate it.
Hey, no problem.
Well, I'll be on my way, then.
[sighs]
If only Chihiro were
his younger sister,
Itsuki probably
wouldn't have ended up
with his little fixation.
A sister's all he needs.
Then again, he probably
wouldn't have become
an author at all
if that were the case.
Talk about complicated.
-[doorbell rings]
-Hmm?
Hey.
I ran into Toki on my way here.
[ITSUKI]
Huh?
Did your meeting
with him go well?
Yeah, totally.
Hmm.
So, what are you makin' tonight?
Either stir-fried shrimp
or paella.
Take a guess at
what was on sale today.
Yeah, shrimp.
[doorbell rings]
Hmm?
Yo.
Hot guy comin' through.
-Hey.
-Come on.
I was trying to be funny.
Play along.
Whoa, smells great!
How are things, Fuwa?
-Good?
-Hey, Chihiro.
Yup.
By the way, I brought a gift.
Mind if I find a place
for it in the fridge?
Oh, not at all!
You do know this is
my apartment, right?
I know, I know.
What's yours is mine.
[HARUTO]
So, how's your new series going?
Itsuki Hashima's first book
where the main heroine
isn't the little sister.
-Just canceled today.
-Really?
I thought the proposal
was pretty promising.
[ITSUKI chuckles]
My heroines being little sisters
is the lifeblood of my work.
-[doorbell rings]
-Hmm?
Must be Kanikou and Miyako.
What a lovely evening this is!
Let's get down
and dirty together.
[gasps]
Nayu!
We just got here,
and you're already on that?
Sounded like
a normal greeting to me.
Silly Myaa.
Yeah, that was
the furthest thing
from a greeting.
Whatever, close
the door behind you.
-Kani!
-Miyako!
Evening. What's up?
Not much.
Good evening to you, too.
By the way, if the mood
ever strikes you,
-feel free to call me "big sis."
-[door closes]
No, thank you.
You might as well get
a head start,
because when Itsuki
and I get married,
you're going to be
my brother-in-law,
and then you'll
pretty much have to.
-No, I won't!
-Shut up!
[NAYUTA]
That sucks!
Your new project's
already been canceled?
Well, these kinds
of things happen.
But I really liked
where the story was going.
[gasps] Hold on,
I just realized something!
This means that aside
from your editor,
I'm the only one
in the whole world who read it!
Yeah, no.
Everyone in this room
read it, too.
Yup.
Yeah, I guess
we all have read it.
I can't believe your story
got around so much.
That manuscript's a whore.
Don't personify my story.
Hey, Chihiro?
How much longer
till dinner's done?
[CHIHIRO]
Uh... around thirty minutes.
Half an hour?
That's a whole lot of time
we have still to kill.
-You wanna make out?
-Just stop.
How about playing a game then?
Does that sound good?
Yeah. Let's do it.
[grunts]
Prince Manwhore here.
He can never take a hint.
Hello pot?
It's the kettle calling again.
Yo, Nayu.
Can you find it in your heart
to stop calling me that?
Great, thanks.
[ITSUKI]
So, what should we play?
[HARUTO]
Hmm? Probably something easy
that we don't need
to spend time setting up.
Oh. Ever heard
of "turtle soup"?
Dude, what?
Weird name.
Now that's Prince Manwhore
for you.
Are you talking about
your little turtle?
Ignore her.
Can you explain it to us?
I certainly can.
Turtle Soup, also known as
a "lateral thinking puzzle"
is a spoken game.
First, the master tells the
story of a mysterious incident.
The other players then ask
yes-or-no questions
about said mysterious incident
and try to solve the mystery
using the information
they've uncovered.
Oh. That's more fun
than the name implies.
[HARUTO] When writers
get together for drinks,
it's pretty common for us
to think up questions
on the spot
to play this game.
It's a good way to flex
your creativity muscles.
But, if you don't come up
with an interesting scenario
or one that sucks,
your writer peers
will berate you
and say stuff like:
"You're not any better
since you won
your newcomer award!"
That part doesn't sound fun.
All right.
Now why don't I give an example?
Ready?
'Cause you're about
to be presented
with a mystery
that will blow your mind!
Ah, you can blow
my mind any time!
Like now!
Get your shit together,
will you?
[clears throat]
Okay. Everyone listen up.
A man gets married.
However, his wife is
a perfect uggo.
She was ugly both
inside and out.
Not a single good quality
to her name.
However, the man lives his life
without complaint.
He has no gripes whatsoever.
Why is that?
-[overlapping chatter]
-[HARUTO] I'm pretty confident
she's a little sister.
Right?
The hell?
How did all three of you
get it right
without asking one question?
Well, your scenario
kinda sucked to begin with.
But I did like the phrasing
"his wife was a perfect uggo,"
because it was sort of funny.
So, I won't go so far
as to insult you personally.
He's just used to writing about
trashy scenarios in his books.
That's not a good excuse.
All right, I've got one,
so I'll go next.
A novelist completely breaks
a deadline.
However, not only does
he not get in trouble,
but his editor
thanks him for it.
Why is that?
Why would they thank him
for missing a deadline?
So weird.
Hey, uh, Prince Manwhore,
is this just a fantasy
for your little turtle?
No.
[NAYUTA] Does this story
take place in modern Japan?
-It does.
-[ITSUKI] You liar!
That is so unrealistic!
I refuse to believe this is
in modern day Japan
with the publishing world
the way it is.
We don't get
a deadline extension
if we step on a land mine!
Come on! True authors
know that better than anyone!
Well, I've never broken
a deadline before, so...
Huh? You're a disgrace
to the profession!
You can be lord of deflowering,
but you won't break a deadline?
That's some value system.
Listen, I'm not a manwhore,
so drop it!
You grow as a person every time
you miss a deadline.
Letting someone down
really makes you reevaluate.
Yeah? Then why do you still
think it's okay to miss them?
[NAYUTA] You'll never break out
of that shell of yours
if you can't learn
to try new things.
Wait. Break out
of my... shell?
-[ITSUKI] Mm-hmm.
-[NAYUTA] Mm-hmm.
What the hell!
Why are you two encouraging me
to make my publisher mad?
[grunts]
Can you just get back
to solving the riddle please?
[ITSUKI] Fine.
Here's a question.
Was the novelist
a little sister?
-[HARUTO] No.
-[ITSUKI] Really?
She's not even a little sister
and they let her slide
on her deadline?
[MIYAKO] He already said
the novelist was a "he"
when he set
the scene earlier.
[ITSUKI]
Oh, that's right.
Then does the novelist
have a little sister?
[HARUTO] Unknown.
He may have one, or may not.
[ITSUKI] All right,
considering it's an unknown,
that's probably not
an important factor.
[MIYAKO] Um, is the novelist
very popular?
[HARUTO]
Unknown.
[MIYAKO] Okay, then is he
the opposite of popular?
[HARUTO]
Unknown.
[MIYAKO]
Those are all unknowns?
Then... do parts
of the novelist's profile,
such as sales, income,
or family life,
have anything to do with it?
-[HARUTO] No.
-[MIYAKO] No?
Hmm. So, his background
is irrelevant.
Okay. Should we ask
about the editorial staff?
[HARUTO]
Oh, you're on the right track.
Oh! I get it!
How's this?
Has the editorial staff
found themselves
in a dangerous situation?
-[HARUTO] Yes.
-Okay then.
Was the editorial staff somehow
saved from this situation
by the novelist
missing this deadline?
-[HARUTO] Yes.
-Yeah!
But I can't think
of any dangerous situation
that could be remedied
by missing a deadline.
Huh.
Missing a deadline
or was it breaking a deadline?
I don't know. Uh...
Haruto, can you tell us
the story again?
Exactly like you did before?
Yeah, sure.
A novelist completely breaks
a deadline.
However, not only does he
not get in trouble,
but his editor
thanks him for it.
Why is that?
Uh-huh, that's what I thought.
So, was this deadline
for a publication?
[chuckles]
No.
Wait. What does that even mean?
[ITSUKI]
Have you solved it too, Kanikou?
-Yeah!
-What?
[ITSUKI]
All right, so did the novelist
physically break
that "deadline?"
[HARUTO]
Yes.
[NAYUTA]
And was the editorial office
completely closed
until the novelist
broke that "deadline"?
[HARUTO]
Yes.
[NAYUTA] When the novelist
broke that "deadline,"
was the entire editorial staff
in a situation
where they couldn't move?
Uh-huh.
You've basically figured it out.
Damn right I figured it out.
But let's go over it
just to be sure.
The editorial office
had its door and windows
completely closed off.
So, all of the staff
had succumbed
to CO2 poisoning
and passed out.
That's when the novelist,
who had come to the office
to explain why he was going
to miss his deadline,
noticed something was wrong.
-He broke through a window...
-[glass shatters]
...and saved
the editorial staff's lives,
who then thanked him
for his heroism.
As any self-respecting author
working here would know,
the Japanese word for "deadline"
can also mean "closed."
So, in this case,
"breaking the deadline"
had a double meaning,
since the author also "breaks"
the "closed" room open.
That's correct.
Good job, man.
Wow. And that was
a tough one!
[laughs]
A simple play on words
is nothing
to someone of my caliber.
-You're so amazing!
-Uhh...
If you've had
enough playing with words,
you can play with me!
I don't bite,
unless you're into that.
[ITSUKI]
No, thank you!
-[NAYUTA] Aww.
-[MIYAKO] Geez, Nayu!
You're like everyone's
drunk pervy uncle!
Ready to start?
[ALL]
Cheers!
[gulping]
Ah! So good!
Oh wow, you aren't kidding.
Mostly sweet with
the right amount of bitterness.
Just be careful.
It may go down easy,
but it's fairly strong.
Delicious.
You made all of this food
by yourself, Chihiro?
Oh, yeah.
That I did.
Ha! You know, Kanikou,
cooking is a really
valuable skill to have.
Oh, that's rich coming from you.
If it's so valuable, why don't
you know a thing about it?
I need motivation!
If I had a little sister
like Kobato from "Haganai"
or Komachi from "Oregairu,"
then I'd be making them
three square meals a day!
[NAYUTA]
I see your obsession influences
all aspects of your life.
Then what if you had
one of the meaner ones
like Kirino from "Oreimo"?
Would you cook for her too?
Oh, Kanikou,
you understand so little.
I'd rather her yell at me
and say something like,
"You can't even cook?
What a worthless piece
of garbage you are!"
Man, you're sick.
Then a little sister
can nurse be back to health!
[sighs]
I am stuffed.
I'm not.
But I bet we could fix that
if you'd let me have
that snake in your pants
for dessert.
-Uh... [coughing]
-[NAYUTA laughing]
Way too forward, Nayu.
You'll scare him off.
-[phone buzzes]
-Hmm?
[HARUTO]
I got a message from my editor.
Okay.
What?
Seriously?
Huh?
[ITSUKI]
They want a new manuscript?
No, all my stuff was accepted.
An anime-related problem
just came up.
And that means
I have to go see my editor ASAP.
Aww. Then you have to leave now?
Must be tough, huh?
Being good enough
to get an anime?
[chuckles]
Sorta.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but that's gonna start
in April, right?
Sure will.
Just under three months away.
Honestly, I'm pretty excited.
Well, give it your all, man.
Back at ya.
[door closes]
[sighs]
I should probably
head home, too.
Oh. It's almost time
for the last bus!
[NAYUTA] All right,
guess I'll see you later.
Be careful getting home.
What are you going to do, Nayu?
I'm holed up in a nearby hotel,
so I'm going to stay
a little longer.
Get some private time.
You're not exactly holed up
if you're here
hanging out with us.
[MIYAKO]
Goodnight.
Thanks for dinner, Chihiro.
You're welcome.
Goodnight!
[giggles]
This is great.
We're finally alone,
like you always wanted!
You should really
get going, too.
Come on. Just think!
We could have quite
the naughty all-nighter.
-[sighs]
-[bottle scraping]
Huh? Hey.
What do you think
you're doing with that, minor?
Don't be such a downer.
A little bit won't hurt!
Not happening.
Stick to apple juice, kid.
[NAYUTA] I'm an adult,
thank you very much.
Not adult enough.
Give me that!
I promise I won't have
more than a sip
if you let it go now.
[BOTH grunt]
[NAYUTA gasps]
Well, that's one way
to get me wet.
Just go clean yourself up.
"Even if I don't have
a place in school,
the whole world lies
ahead of me"?
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
Aah!
[NAYUTA] Oh, Itsuki.
I love you.
And yet you're only interested
in little sisters.
You're probably the most
perverted person I've ever met.
Get a good look in
while you can!
Until tomorrow.
Go do some work, you dummy.
I'm in love.
With your work, Hashima.
-Why the pause?
-[gagging]
-Huh?
[NAYUTA retching]
[ITSUKI]
Ah, come on!
I still can't believe
she puked on me day one.
I'm sorry about what happened
the other night.
[laughs]
It's okay.
I'm not the kind of guy
who stresses about
the little things.
I like you.
I have ever since I started
reading your books.
I fell in love
with your words at once.
So, will you please
go out with me?
Uh... Uh...
Uh, well...
let me get back
to you on that one.
[sobbing] What should do?
What do I tell her?
I mean, I don't know
the first thing about this chick
aside from the color
of her puke!
A girlfriend can't just be hot,
she's gotta have
a good personality, too!
Oh.
So, this is her debut work.
[sighs]
Hmm.
[chuckles]
Huh?
Uh...
[sniffles]
This is on another level.
Well, then.
Guess I'll get back to work.