[ITSUKI]
When I was in sixth grade,
my mother was so ill
she had to be hospitalized.
On top of that, my father would
come home late because of work,
so we hired a housekeeper.
[MITAHORA]
You can't always
leave your
vegetables on the plate.
[ITSUKI]
I told you I don't like them,
Miss Mitahora.
I asked you not to put them in.
Do you want to grow up to be
big and strong, or not?
Thought so. Eat up.
You look tougher already!
Could you at least
stop cooking carrots
and green peppers
into the meat?
It tastes weird.
[sighs]
My second year of middle school,
my mother passed away.
I couldn't make any friends,
with how pathetic
I looked all the time.
So...
I always went straight home
after school and read books.
When a book really sucked me in,
I could leave my harsh
life behind for a bit.
I fell in love with all
of the beautiful girls
in these stories.
And I often took
the most interest
in the little sister characters.
[sighs]
If I were the author,
I'd have the protagonist
and the little sister
get together.
Not that I could ever
write a novel.
[birds chirping]
[doorbell rings]
[doorbell rings continuously]
[grunts]
Ayane Mitahora.
Nice to meet you!
Mitahora?
Like...? Oh!
Yeah!
Like your housekeeper.
I'm her daughter!
Freshman in high school!
And you must be Itsuki Hashima.
Yeah, that would be me.
What are you doing here?
I just came to
hang out with you.
What? Hang out?
I heard that you've
been down lately.
So I came to try
and cheer you up!
Our housekeeper sent
her daughter to cheer me up?
That's kinda strange.
No, she had nothing
to do with this.
I came here all on my own.
-Uh.
-[giggles]
She almost never stops
talking about you at home
so I had to come meet you.
Like how you got
a hundred on a test,
and how good a kid you are
for doing your homework.
She's always comparing me
with you,
like we're both her kids.
So naturally,
I started to think of you
as my responsible little bro.
I don't know if I'm happy
to be thought of like that.
Who wouldn't be worried
if someone they considered
a little brother
was feeling down?
I couldn't allow that.
So here I am!
Wow that's really... nice.
This came out of nowhere,
so obviously I was shocked.
But she was going out of her way
to help a total stranger,
just like the heroes
and heroines of the stories
I'd loved to read.
[AYANE] Wow, you sure have
a lot of manga.
[ITSUKI] They aren't manga,
they're novels.
Not that it matters.
[AYANE]
Oh, really? Hmm.
I didn't know they made
novels like this.
Yeah, that one's a little off.
Not my usual stuff.
Oh, I get it,
you're embarrassed.
Trust me,
there's no reason to be.
I borrow indecent manga
from my friends all the time.
Really? You do?
Um-hmm.
Hmm.
Maybe I'll try reading
some of these, too.
Do you think I could borrow one?
[ITSUKI]
Huh?
Uh, sure, I guess.
[AYANE]
Thanks!
[ITSUKI]
One sec, I'll find something.
Hmm.
Since you're new, let's start
with a shorter story.
Maybe a light fantasy?
I bet you'd connect with
a school story more.
Maybe you'd prefer
a female protagonist, too.
Come on, you don't have to
devote so much energy to it.
Of course I do.
Hmm?
Well, what if you don't like
the one I pick out?
You can just let me
borrow something else.
But for now, I think I'd like
to read the one
you're most into at the moment.
[ITSUKI]
The one that I'm the most into?
[AYANE]
Yeah.
Umm...
That'd be this.
[AYANE]
"A Sister's All You Need"?
A little sister?
Do you want one?
I guess you could say that.
Then could I borrow this one?
I'll be done by next week!
You mean you're coming back
next week?
Can't I?
[grunts]
Well, if you really want to.
[doorbell rings]
From then on,
Ayane Mitahora came over
to my house every week.
She was a pretty high school
girl who'd hang out with me.
We'd talk about light novels.
She'd even cosplay for me,
every once in a while.
So, as you might expect,
young Itsuki Hashima
fell head over heels.
Any boy would.
I'm definitely
telling her next week.
[sighs]
Hey, uh...
Did something bad happen?
[chuckles]
[grunts]
Well...
I asked my crush out
and got rejected.
And I just can't seem
to let it go.
[chuckles]
You confessed to someone?
Yeah.
What kind of person are they?
He's a boy in
the same class as me.
He's short and not
super good-looking,
and he works
in the library.
I think I must have
fallen for him
when I saw him reading
a light novel on the bus.
[gasps]
[AYANE]
I've caught myself thinking
about him ever since.
He was always working hard,
even when the other kids
fooled around
instead of getting ready
for the cultural fair.
And he's the only one who really
cleaned up when it was over.
But he'd go straight home
as soon as he was done
with his assigned task.
He never quite followed
the crowd--
Okay, I get it!
You're the one
who asked about it.
I...
-Uh.
I like you a whole lot, Ayane.
Huh?
You know.
I mean I like, like you.
So will you go out with me?
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
Wait, what do you mean?
I'd bet anything that I've read
more light novels than that guy.
And I'm not super
good-looking, either.
And I know for a fact that
I'll never follow the crowd!
[whimpers]
Listen, it's not you, it's me.
The truth is,
I just can't see you as anything
but my little brother.
♪
Sorry.
I'll see you later.
Don't ever come here again!
I have never needed
an older sister.
Itsuki, I--
[ITSUKI]
Yeah.
A little sister's all I need.
[AYANE]
But...
you don't have a little sister.
[door shuts]
[ITSUKI whimpers, grunts]
Why would a beautiful girl
fall for a boring guy
who likes reading?
This isn't some stupid novel.
She even got rejected!
What does that make me?
The protagonist rejects
a minor character,
whose mom works
for my family.
I'm not a minor character.
I'm not even
a background character.
Damn it all.
I wanna be the protagonist.
I guess.
I'll try writing.
[typing]
It was as though I had
a revelation of sorts.
[typing continues]
There wasn't really
a logic to it.
But I was certain I could write
something in that moment.
My fantasies and love
for little sisters.
My failures, frustrations.
My inferiority complex.
My longing to become
the protagonist.
And my overwhelming sense of
hope that pushed me forward.
I wanted to give everything I
had to the story in front of me.
Just you wait, world.
You'll see.
I'm the protagonist!
[sighs]
[gasps]
[ITSUKI]
Kanikou.
I didn't realize
you were already here.
Yeah, I could tell.
I take it you had a nice dream?
Yeah, sorta.
[NAYUTA]
Hmm? What kind of dream was it?
It was all about my ex.
[gasps]
I'm kidding.
I dreamt about the old me.
Felt like a completely
different person.
As you all know,
they've finally decided
to make "Mahou Academy"
into an anime.
So let's toast to me entering
a new chapter in my life!
-Cheers!
Congrats, big bro.
Yeah. Congrats.
Thank you all so much!
You know this was supposed
to be kept a secret, right?
Yet you immediately
opened your big mouth.
Come on, it's not
that big a deal.
At least I didn't
post about it online.
Just try to show
a little restraint, moron.
[ITSUKI] Well, we've got plenty
more years to work on that!
[TOKI]
You're damn right, we do.
We're gonna be so busy,
you'll wanna drop dead.
You'd better be prepared.
Despite how these two usually
treat each other,
they do get along well.
That sounds like
it could be kind of nice.
-[water running]
-[dishes clanging]
I thought I'd bring you
over a little present!
It's an indie board game
I found the other day.
Seemed appropriate
for your new beginnings.
"The Life of
a Light Novel Writer," huh?
This game already sounds
sad and bleak.
True.
But even so,
we might as well try it.
From the looks of it, it's a lot
like your standard dice game.
[MIYAKO] Yeah, I think I've
played one just like it.
The person with the most money
at the end wins, right?
[HARUTO]
Nope!
In this game,
there are other values,
like popularity and happiness
that affect the outcome.
The game lasts for 30 rounds
and the player who gets the most
happiness points by the end
is declared the winner.
[CHIHIRO] Then what do you use
the money for?
[HARUTO] Apparently, you can
pay to have your dice roll
increased a little.
[ITSUKI]
Ah. Gotta remember that.
There's a lot of detailed rules.
But let's jump in.
It says that the youngest
player goes first.
Well, that'd be me, then!
All right, where do
I place my piece?
[HARUTO] There's major,
mid-level, and minor labels,
or you can be
an internet novelist.
Each starts on
the "Newcomer Prize" space.
And you can even switch
courses later, if you want.
[CHIHIRO] Then I think I'll
start at the mid-level label.
Let's see.
I gotta roll a four to debut.
Meaning the game
doesn't even start
until you win
the newcomer award.
Show me a four.
-[gasps]
-[dice clatter]
[CHIHIRO]
Yes! I successfully debuted!
All right, I'm up next.
I might as well go
for the major label.
I mean, why not?
So I need to roll a six.
You make it sound so easy.
Well, in real life, the chances
are more like a hundred to one.
So these odds aren't
all that bad.
[NAYUTA exclaims]
[ITSUKI]
Seriously?
[NAYUTA chuckles]
Then I might as well go
for an astronomical debut
at a major label, too!
[grunts]
These guys don't know
what they're missing.
I have a freakin' anime.
That entry barrier's too high.
I think I'll go for
a minor label instead.
And I've debuted!
[sighs]
Then I guess I'll try out
the internet novelist route
since no one's gone
for that yet.
Oh cool, I don't even
need to roll.
And that concludes round one.
Okay, back to me.
[ALL laugh]
[CHIHIRO]
Great!
I released a new volume
and got 500,000 yen.
[HARUTO]
Nice. Here's your cash.
[NAYUTA]
Oh, hey!
I released a new volume too!
But I got three million yen.
That's quite the difference,
despite them both being newbies.
Well, that's one more reason
to go for a major label!
A five?
That's so close!
Guess it's my turn again.
Let's see.
I got two 200,000 yen
for releasing a new volume.
It must be tough to work
for a minor label.
-[HARUTO] And it's my go.
-[TOKI snoring]
[HARUTO] Hey, someone said
they enjoyed my work.
I gain one happiness point.
And that ends round two.
My story creates a buzz,
so my popularity goes up a rank.
So what does it mean
when my popularity goes up?
[HARUTO] Apparently,
you can get more royalties
and extra bonuses
when you roll the die.
Huh. That sounds good.
I just made one million
because of reprints.
I failed to debut again.
Uhh.
Just 200,000 again.
Uploaded a novel online.
Nothing really happens.
Rejected again.
Rejected again!
Again.
Again!
Rejected... again.
Dude, give it up.
Go try the minor
or mid-level labels.
No way!
I'm sure if I don't give up,
my dreams will come true!
But you're letting everyone else
get way ahead of you here.
Like for example: Nayu,
how much money do you have?
Something like
20 million yen.
-[ITSUKI] Twenty mil?
-Major labels, man.
And all I've got is 300,000
from my side gig.
But you're still the most
popular one of us,
aren't you, Fuwa?
[MIYAKO] I guess each route
is a little different.
You don't earn much on
the internet novelist route,
but it's easy
to get popular.
You have a lot of money
and popularity at a major label,
but neither at a minor.
Yeah, sorry for being
such a winner.
But you'll get used to it.
[dice clatter]
Let's see.
I missed a deadline,
so I miss five turns,
and lose three happiness points?
Don't you think that's
a bit too harsh
for just missing a deadline?
[MIYAKO]
What do you mean "just"?
At major labels, publishing
gets really strict.
I've heard that if
you miss a deadline,
they might not let you release
a book for another year.
Well, good to know it's not all
sunshine and rainbows there.
I think I'll go for
a mid-level label now.
What ever happened
to following your dreams?
[ITSUKI]
Oh. Six.
Hey.
I just got an offer
from a mid-level label.
[sighs]
Being a 'net novelist
is pretty comfortable.
But you know what?
I'm goin' for it.
My series is now an anime!
And I get two million yen,
too, yeah!
They're making my series
into a live-action movie!
And I get a million yen!
But I miss two turns and lose
three happiness points?
Wait, what's going on?
These stupid trolls
are flooding my blog!
If my popularity
is higher than six,
I lose three happiness points,
miss two turns,
and my popularity rank
drops by two?
What did I do to deserve
such a terrible fate?
Win a million betting on horses?
What does that have to do
with being a writer?
My editor lost my manuscript!
I miss two turns and lose
five happiness points?
[ITSUKI]
Oof.
That's pretty depressing.
[CHIHIRO] My media venture
falls through
because my editor screwed up.
Minus five happiness points.
Could you not, editor?
I kinda feel bad.
I know this is a game,
and you just drew a
completely random unlucky event,
but I'm still sorry
about your editor.
My anime was a failure.
Minus five happiness points.
Hey look.
Just like me.
Looks like my publisher
got bought out.
And now I get to go
to a major label
and start a brand new story.
I'm not sure if this is
a good thing or a bad thing.
[CHIHIRO] Because
the protagonist of my book
didn't end up
with the heroine they wanted,
I ended up getting a stalker.
So I lose three turns and four
points from my happiness meter.
Geez, a stalker?
Does that kind of thing
actually happen?
[TOKI] And things
only got worse from there
for our band
of troubled writers.
Until...
Finally done!
[CHIHIRO]
I swear, I had no idea
want the readers wanted
from me after a while.
[HARUTO] I never should have
published my book.
I should have just treasured
my time on the internet scene.
[MIYAKO]
So who won this thing, anyway?
Didn't we say that the person
with the most
happiness points wins?
[MIYAKO] Wait,
everyone's in the negatives?
[CHIHIRO]
Makes sense.
Most of the events
took points away.
I barely remember
anything positive.
Yeah, and since
Itsuki took forever to debut,
he just didn't have
as many chances
for anything bad
to happen to him.
I know I won the game
and everything,
but I don't feel good.
And this game is...
Yeah.
It's pretty damn realistic.
I hate to say it,
but I have seen most of
the game's events happen.
What? That's crazy!
Is the life of a writer
really this bad?
Yeah. It's not exactly easy to
be happy with a job like this.
[MIYAKO]
It sounds so hard.
Well...
we wouldn't still be here
if it wasn't fun, too.
You've got such a good attitude,
Itsuki!
Get off me, Kanikou!
[NAYUTA] Nope!
I'm gonna get even closer!
I'm gonna crawl in your mouth,
so open up!
[laughs]
Well, this is my stop.
I'll see you all later.
-Bye! Get home safe!
-See you around!
[joyful squeals, laughter]
Sorry, you guys.
Go on without me!
[MIYAKO]
Um, Mr. Toki?
Yes?
Could you tell me more
about what it's like
to be an editor sometime?
I'd love to learn about it.
Yeah, sure, no problem.
You thinking about
being one yourself?
Yes.
Okay.
Then want to work
part-time at our office?
Yeah!
[giggling]
Out of everyone
in the whole world,
Itsuki loves me!
And that's a fact!
He just needs to become
a protagonist like me.
I don't know what that'll mean,
since he's always been the best
writer in the universe to me.
I guess I'll just have
to keep inspiring him.
I don't want to lose.
At all.
[MAN 1] What?
You're seriously buying that?
Wasn't the anime terrible,
though?
[MAN 2]
That anime never happened!
But, dude, the novels
still kick ass.
I gotta try harder.
[fast typing]
Huh?
"Mahou Academy"'s
gonna be an anime?
Seriously?
This is real right now?
-[TOKI] Yeah.
-Hell, yes!
My time has finally come!
[TOKI] Let me tell you
the whole story first.
This opportunity only came up
because another
anime project fell through.
So basically,
you're the replacement.
There's really
no time or budget,
and frankly, the chances of it
being a success are low.
Plus, the whole thing with Fuwa.
So do you wanna do this?
I do.
[TOKI]
You sure?
You can't know how things'll
turn out if you don't try.
So you bet your ass
I'm gonna try.
What I said sounded cool
and all, but...
No, it'll be okay.
I can get through this.
After all, I don't
have a little sister.
And as long as I have
this yearning for one,
I can keep going forever!
Yeah.
Now let's do this!
[typing]
I have to tell Itsuki the truth!