( Energy pulsing )
¶
( Red knights yelling )
( All gasp )
Dark Knight: Who are you people?
( Gags )
( Red Knight chuckles )
Charge!
Red Knight 2: Kick their asses!
Dark Knight: Hold on!
You're supposed to be
on our side!
( All shouting )
Bercouli: Damn. What's going on?
Where'd they come from?
( Asuna gasps )
Oh, no.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
- ( Pugilist gags )
- Red Knight: Dude...
That's awesome!
Red Knight 2: So gross.
( Asuna gasps )
( Grunts )
( Chorus vocalizing )
¶
( soldiers screaming )
( Tone whines )
( Tones whining )
( Asuna gasping )
I can't stop now.
( Panting )
( Gasps )
Alice!
Alice: You must stop right now.
Let us handle them.
Stay here, and rest a bit.
Asuna: But I can't.
I just realized
who those red knights are.
They're not from here.
They're from my world.
( Alice gasps )
That may be,
but they are
just a bloodthirsty mob
flailing their swords.
No matter
how great their number,
there is nothing to fear.
- Bercouli: She's right.
- Asuna: Huh?
Bercouli: Relax, little lady.
Let us knights
take a crack at 'em.
( Asuna sighs )
( Alice grunts )
Asuna: Thank you. Be careful.
Bercouli: Troops!
I want a tight formation!
We'll bust through their ranks!
Soldiers: Ho!
¶
( all grunting, yelling )
( Pugilist gags )
( Iskahn gasps )
( Growls )
( Screams )
( Eye humming )
I-I gotta tell the emperor.
Have to call this off.
( Wings flap )
( Tones whining )
( Iskahn groaning )
( Screams )
Dampa: Ch-champion!
( Iskahn gasps )
( Grunting )
( Dampa gasps )
( Iskahn moans )
( Screams )
( Gasping )
Dampa: Ch-champion. ( Gasps )
Iskahn: We didn't get
any orders from the emperor
about those red bastards,
did we?
Dampa: No. He didn't
say anything about 'em.
Iskahn: Thought so.
Then if we decided
to go and slaughter 'em all,
he shouldn't have
a problem with that.
Dampa: I guess not.
Iskahn: We're gonna
save our people
on the other side
of the canyon.
Soon as the bridge goes up,
I want everyone
to charge to the other side.
Dampa: But what bridge?
There ain't no--
Iskahn: There will be.
I'll ask someone to make it.
¶
no time to shimmy across a rope.
I'll have to jump
across it instead!
( Yells )
( Gasps )
Dampa: Champion!
( Grunting )
( Yells )
Iskahn: Huh?
( Grunts )
( Asuna grunts )
Red Knight: God damn it!
¶
( Soldiers yelling )
( Soldiers gasp )
( Red knights murmuring )
( Asuna gasps )
¶
stop it.
( Soldier wails )
Asuna: Stop it!
( Soldier shrieks )
¶
Red Knight: Later, babe!
- Hah!
- ( Asuna screams )
( Groaning )
( Iskahn grunts )
Hah!
They're weaker than they look.
( Asuna gasps )
He's from the dark territory.
( Iskahn gasps )
( Yells )
Asuna: No way.
( Gasps )
Iskahn: I need your help.
Asuna: For what?
- Uh...
- Iskahn: You're the one
that made those little mountains
and the canyon behind me, right?
Asuna: Yeah.
Iskahn: All right,
here's the deal.
I need you to make a bridge
across the canyon for my people.
Do that, and my 4,000 Pugilists
will cross over
and help you fight.
We'll crush
these red bastards together.
Asuna: You'll help?
But you're the enemy
Sheyta: I do not think
this one is the type to lie.
Iskahn: Hey, there.
Asuna: Uh...
Okay, then.
I'll help your people
cross over.
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Pugilists cheering )
Alice: They are indifferent,
heartless.
( Breathes deeply )
Fiends...
Begone!
( Yells )
System call.
Discharge.
From the top of that hill,
I can incinerate them all.
Make way!
Bercouli: Wait! It's not sa--
( wings beat )
No! Alice!
( Alice gasps )
Enhance arma--
( gasping )
Bercouli: Bastard!
I'm gonna kill you for this!
( Chorus vocalizing )
Out of my way, or--
Renly: Release recollection!
Commander, go after her.
Bercouli: Thanks, kid.
Watch your back!
( Whistles )
( Dragons roar )
Bercouli: Don't lose 'em!
( Gabriel chuckles )
¶
( tone whines )
( Energy humming )
Asuna: Nice tactics.
Iskahn: Yeah, well,
I trained 'em myself.
Look, they got us
hemmed in here,
so south's the only way to go.
We'll have to take 'em all on
at some point,
but there's so many,
it ain't gonna be easy.
Asuna: We'll break
through the lines
and head south like you said,
then put as much distance
between us and them as we can.
As soon as we're
far enough away,
I'll try to make
another canyon to block them.
Soldier: I bring a message!
( Grunts )
Milady Alice has been taken.
Emperor Vecta snatched her up
and flew off with her.
The spotters saw his dragon
heading due south.
Asuna: What?!
Iskahn: That's where we're--
wait! He took off with her?
Then when I saw him, he wasn't
just checking out the battle!
Hey, woman!
Your Alice is the priestess
of light, ain't she?
The whole point of my people
being here was to catch her.
Why does the emperor
want her so bad?
Wh-what'll happen
when he gets her?
Asuna: This world'll be...
- Destroyed.
- ( Iskahn gasps )
Asuna: That's vecta's plan,
to take Alice,
the Priestess of Light
down to the World's End Altar.
And once there,
this world and everything in it
is going to be wiped out.
Sheyta: A dragon
cannot fly forever.
And with passengers,
they only last half a day.
- ( Gloves clank )
- Iskahn: Right.
Then I guess
you should get goin'
while the gettin's good!
Asuna: You'd let us go,
just like that?
But you're
from the dark territory,
and he's your emperor.
You're talking treason.
Iskahn: I don't know about that.
At the start of this,
vecta gave
his council of ten an order
that all he wanted
was this Priestess of Light.
And now that he's
got what he wanted,
I'd say his order to us has
been fulfilled. Wouldn't you?
Me and my people
are free to do whatever now,
so if we wanted to help you
and the human army
steal the priestess back
from the emperor, we could.
The choice is up to us.
( Chuckles )
Right?
( Asuna gasps )
( Glove creaks )
Iskahn: I--
we can't disobey the emperor.
If he tells us
we have to fight you,
then my people have to obey,
or he'll kill us.
But here's
what we can do for you.
We'll keep
the red guys busy here
while you and the human army
catch up to the emperor.
When you do you,
you tell him, that bastard,
we're through dyin' for nothin'!
You tell him
we ain't his puppets no more!
( Pugilists yelling )
Iskahn: Now we're talkin'.
That's it, people!
Keep that line open, you hear?!
( Sighs ) There's your exit,
but you better hurry up.
We can't hold it forever.
Asuna: Thank you.
Sheyta: I think
I will stay here with him.
Asuna: All right, then.
Good luck, and stay safe.
( Armies yelling )
Iskahn: You sure
about this, woman?
Sheyta: Stop it.
You know my name.
Iskahn: You sure
about this, Sheyta?
'Cause there's no guarantee
you'll survive this.
Sheyta: I cannot
let anyone else slash you.
Only I reserve the right to.
Iskahn: Hah! Says you!
( Sheyta chuckles )
( Iskahn chuckles )
Come on!
Show me some fire, Pugilists!
( Pugilists yelling )
Iskahn: Get in a circle!
Defense position!
If any of 'em tries to attack,
- wind up, and give 'em hell!
- ( Pugilists cheering )
Dampa: Ready to kick
some ass, champion?
( Joints crack )
- ( Gloves clank )
- Iskahn: Yeah.
( Vassago moaning )
Critter: Morning, sunshine.
You were out for a while there.
Say something so I know
your brain didn't get fried.
Vassago: Asshole.
( Groans ) Damn it.
I died. I fell down
some bottomless pit.
Critter: Ooh, that sounds
both horrible and pathetic.
You know, you been out
for eight hours now.
Vassago: Wait. Eight hours?
Critter: Why do you look
so panicked, man?
Everything's cool.
Right before
you got your ass owned in there,
I dialed the time
back down to one-to-one.
Vassago: What? Son of a bitch!
What the hell are you messin'
around with the time for?!
- ( Critter gags )
- Vassago: In 12 hours,
the JSDF is gonna bust in here,
and they'll be gunnin' for us!
Critter: I know.
I've been keeping up.
I cranked the time down 'cause
Captain Miller ordered me to.
Using our satellite connection,
I just logged a bunch
of players from the U.S.
Into the dark territory.
Vassago: The hell for?
( Critter chuckles )
That's a log of you
and the cap's movements
in there.
A few minutes ago,
he passed the place you croaked
and is heading due south.
And get this.
He's not traveling
with the dark territory's army.
He's on his own,
and you know what that means.
Vassago: He could be chasing
after Alice, or he's got her.
Either way,
you should crank up the time.
Critter: Nope. Not yet.
We have a problem. Check it out.
That part in red
is what's left
of the U.S. players,
and that black circle
half-surrounded by 'em
is a chunk
of the dark territory's army.
Our problem is that white dot.
That's the human army,
or what's left of 'em.
According to the log,
there's about 700, give or take.
If they catch up to the Captain,
that would be no bueno.
They gotta be stopped asap.
Vassago: Then you
better get to it.
What you got in mind?
( Critter laughs )
I got us a second batch
of U.S. players on standby.
When there's 20 thou,
I'll drop 'em
on top of the human army.
That's 28 times their numbers.
It's gonna be
a friggin' massacre!
Then I'll crank time up
to 1,000-to-one.
We'll sit back and
let the Captain do his thing.
He'll have all the time
in the world and then some
to get Alice
to the Southern terminal.
Vassago: I hope it goes
as smooth as you say.
The human side's army
is a hell of a lot tougher
than you think.
Hell, those integrity knights
are straight-up bad-asses.
I sat there and watched
as they mowed down
the dark territory's front line.
We lost thousands
in one gigantic flash of--
flash of--( Gasps )
Lightning Flash!
It's her!
It totally was!
I'll never forget that bitch.
Critter: What? Who are
you talking about? ( Groans )
Vassago: Guess what,
you little four-eyed freak.
I just figured out
the rath guys in subcon
are doin' the same thing we are.
Yeah, but they got
Japanese vrmmo players logged in
and working with the human army.
- Critter: No way!
- Vassago: And I'll bet,
if Lightning Flash Asuna's
in there,
that dual-wielding bastard
is, too.
( Laughs ) This is great!
It's my lucky day.
I'm goin' back in, baby,
- so get me prepped.
- ( Critter growls )
Vassago: Send me
to the human army's location
with the second batch
of players.
Critter: Okay, if you want,
but you wasted
the only Dark Knight account
we had, remember?
All I got is a basic grunt like
the others, so no complaining.
Vassago: I ain't using
one of those accounts.
I got a special one instead.
¶
( Horse neighs )
( Asuna gasps )
( Gasps ) Whoa!
( Energy pulsing )
¶
( Renly gasps )
I leave the rest to you.
( Dragon roars )
Liena: Oh, no!
Sir Renly
is going to barrel through them.
Asuna: Don't!
( Renly gasps )
( Energy pulsing )
( Armies gasping )
( Asuna gasps )
( Soldiers gasping )
Sinon: No rapid-fire? Oh, well.
I guess I'm more used
to single-shot weapons, anyway.
¶
( Asuna gasps )
Sinon: I'm late. Sorry.
( Asuna laughs )
Shinonon!
( Singing in Japanese )
¶
( Vassago chuckles )