ｶ
( typing )
Aki: Are you ready for this?
Asuna: Yeah.
Ready as I'll ever be.
Higa: Okay, Asuna,
a couple reminders
before I log you in.
You're using
superuser account zero-one,
Stacia, the Goddess of creation.
You'll have admin privileges
that include unlimited
manipulation of the landscape,
but be careful with it.
When you change the terrain,
the flow of the mnemonic data
between your S.T.L.
And the underworld's main
visualizer is gonna be massive.
I'm talking "overloading
your fluctlight" massive.
You should be fine if you change
the terrain up a few times.
Just try not to overdo it.
You'll know you are
if your head starts hurting.
If it does, stop. Got it?
Asuna: Got it.
Aki: All right.
It's up to you now.
Go get him.
( Asuna chuckles )
See you in a bit.
( Cover grinding )
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Girls shuddering )
ｶ
( singing in Japanese )
( Asuna gasps )
( Groans )
I guess I overdid it
on the first try.
Whatever. Now that I'm here,
I have to find Kirito.
Tiese: Lady Stacia?
Are you her,
the Goddess, Stacia?
( Asuna sighs ) No, I'm sorry.
I'm definitely not a Goddess.
Ronie: But you--i mean,
you just performed a miracle!
Everyone owes you their lives!
You saved the guards
and the priests and me
- and my mentor Kirito, too.
- ( Asuna gasps )
Actually, Kirito's
the reason I'm here.
I need to see him now,
so please take me to him!
I know he's not well,
but I think I can help,
so let me see him.
( Girls sigh )
( Girls grunt )
Right.
Come with us.
ｶ
( Asuna gasps )
Kirito?
( Kirito gasping )
A-a-
a-a-a...
( Gasping )
( Asuna gasps )
It's all right, Kirito.
I'm here now.
( Kirito sighs )
( Asuna crying )
Thank you both for keeping him
safe and letting me see him.
Ronie: Um, if you're
not lady Stacia,
then who are you,
and where are you from?
Asuna: My name is Asuna.
I'm human, just like you,
and I come
from the same place as Kirito,
not from this world,
another one.
Both: You're not from here,
and neither is he?
Ronie: But what world?
The only other one is heaven.
Is that where you're from,
the home of the three
goddesses of creation,
the gods who control
the elements, and the angels?
Asuna: Whoa, hold on!
He and I aren't from heaven
or any place like it.
I'm sorry. It's kind of
complicated to explain.
Maybe the best thing
would be for me to talk
to whoever's in charge here.
Can you take me to them?
Ronie: Yes, of course!
Please follow us.
We'll take you right to him.
Asuna: Don't worry, 'kay?
I'll be right back. Promise.
I'll figure this out somehow.
( Gasps )
Tiese: Wait!
She means no harm, milady!
Ronie: She's not the enemy!
She's here to help, lady Alice!
( Asuna gasps ) Alice?
Alice: Who are you?
What do you want with Kirito?!
( Asuna gasps )
Back off. Now!
Kirito is mine! Understand!
Alice: Ridiculous!
Begone from here!
Girls: Uh...
Bercouli: Well, well, well.
Now, that is a heck of a sight.
Two beautiful flowers in bloom.
( Both grunt )
Bercouli: So gorgeous.
So dangerous.
( Grunts )
( Both gasp )
Alice: Why do you
stop me, uncle?
Do not trust her.
She is a spy for the enemy!
Bercouli:
Would you relax, kiddo?
She's definitely
not working for the bad guys.
Didn't you see
what happened out there?
She saved everyone's lives...
Including mine.
ｶ
here they come.
( Chuckles )
- ( Chorus vocalizing )
- ( Gasps )
( Gasps )
This rainbow appeared,
and when it hit the ground,
it cracked it open
for a hundred mels.
It made a gap so wide,
those pugilists
couldn't even jump it.
We were this close
to being wiped out,
and she stopped it.
There's no denying that.
We owe this lady our thanks.
Alice: What are you implying?
She is either an enemy spy
or some filthy heretic
posing as a divine entity,
but there is no way
she is the Goddess Stacia!
( Asuna grunts )
Bercouli: Didn't say she was.
Think about it. If this
little lady was a real Goddess,
she'd be scarier
than the pontifex.
She'd break you in half
for bein' rude to her.
Then she'd chuck your ass
into that pit she conjured.
( Alice groans )
( Asuna gasps )
( Alice sighs )
Asuna: True. I may look it,
but I'm not a Goddess.
I'm a human being,
just like you.
That said,
I am from another world,
and I know things
about your situation you don't.
Bercouli: Hmm.
We should hear her out.
In fact, the other knights
and the unit captains
should be part of this.
We can discuss it
over some tea.
Alice: Right. As you wish.
Bercouli: Great.
Now that that's settled,
- I need your help, ladies.
- Girls: Huh?
Bercouli: Get some tea
and some booze for me,
and bring back it to my tent.
You might as well stay
for the meeting, too.
Girls: Yes, sir!
Alice: Let me be clear.
If you would like to see Kirito,
you must ask
my permission first.
His safety is my responsibility,
regardless of who you are.
( Asuna grunts ) That does it.
I don't need
your permission to see him.
He's not yours!
Alice: Perhaps he
should decide that.
( Asuna gasps )
Yes, perhaps he should.
Both: Hmph.
( Girls sigh )
Tiese: Wow. That's all
we needed, more tension.
Oh, well! Time to go
and boil some water.
You start that,
and I'll get the liquor jug.
- Okay? Okay!
- Ronie: Uh...
But Kirito's my mentor.
ｶ
Asuna: It's nice
to meet you all.
My name is Asuna,
and I come
from a world outside yours,
a human world, but you
can't physically get to it.
My home, the real world,
and yours, the underworld,
are two totally separate
planes of existence.
( Scattered gasping )
Asuna: As we speak,
there's a battle going on
in the real world.
It's between two groups,
and they're both fighting
for control of the underworld.
I'm here on behalf of one of
the groups. They're called rath.
Golgorosso:
Is that why you're here then,
to take over our world
and rule over it?
Asuna: No, not at all.
My group and I, we want
to protect the underworld.
The people
we're fighting against
don't care about this place.
They just want
one of your people,
and when they find them,
they'll capture them
and bring them into our world,
then destroy yours.
Golgorosso:
That's monstrous.
Captain: I don't believe this.
Captain 2: How do we know
she speaks the truth?
Bercouli: 'Cause it's possible.
The dark territory
surrounds the human empire.
It's basically a whole
'nother world from ours,
a place with folks who just
wanna invade and destroy us.
Few of us have ever seen it
or been to it,
but it's as real
as our side of the mountains.
And now we find out
there's another world out there.
I say sure, why not?
You said
these folks you're fighting
are looking
for someone specific.
You got any idea
who that could be?
( Asuna grunts )
( Alice gasps )
Uh, I am the one?!
- ( Captains murmuring )
- Bercouli: So that's what
this "priestess of light"
stuff's about.
Look, there isn't
much time left.
There's only one way
to keep the underworld safe,
and that's for Alice to return
to the real world with me
as quickly as possible.
Once the enemy
finds out she's not here,
they'll give up
and leave your world alone.
Alice: Y-you must be joking!
You want me to run away
to your so-called "real world,"
to abandon my people
when they need me the most?
I would never!
I am an integrity knight!
My one and only duty
is to protect the human empire!
Asuna: And you'd be doing that.
I'm sorry.
I wish there were another way,
but if the enemy
from the real world finds you,
they'll take you,
and then everything here,
the people, the land, the sky,
everything,
they will erase it all!
We have to go right now,
before they find you!
Bercouli: Hold on there!
It seems your information's
a bit out of date, little lady.
The enemy from your world,
yeah, they already found her.
( Asuna gasps )
( Bercouli sighs )
Everything makes
a lot more sense now.
It all fits. The priestess
of light and the dark god vecta.
That's why he suddenly
showed up to lead his army,
but he's not a dark god.
He came from the real world,
just like you.
Asuna: Dark god vecta?
Then the dark territory
has superuser accounts,
and they're not locked.
Renly: Um,
m-may I ask something?
Regarding
this priestess of light,
I have never heard
of her before.
So why do these invaders
from the real world
want Alice,
of all people, so badly?
Sheyta: She broke the seal
in her right eye.
Alice: Y-you know
of what happened?
And the seal? But how?
Sheyta: The central cathedral
is indestructible,
made of
the hardest material here.
I think how fun it would be
to slice through it.
Then, all of a sudden,
I feel a horrible pain
in my right eye.
( Captains stammer )
( Bercouli chuckles ) I wonder,
how many of us here experienced
the same thing as her?
I'm sure at some point you all
had doubts about the pontifex
or some of the church's laws.
You saw flashes of red light
in your right eye,
and then you felt the pain.
It hurt so bad,
it made you forget
what you were thinkin' about,
didn't it?
You know what happens
if you keep thinking
those blasphemous thoughts?
The pain gets worse and worse
until it's searing your brain.
And then...
Alice: Your vision turns red,
and your right eye explodes.
( All gasping )
Renly: Then did your eye...
Alice: Mm-hmm.
To put a stop
to administrator's rule,
I knew I would be confronting
chudelkin as well as her.
To muster the resolve to do so,
I had to lose my eye. ( Gasps )
Come to think of it,
I recall administrator
saying something,
something about
the seal of the eye.
I believe she said, "code...
That's it! Code 8-7-1!
She looked right at me,
and that is what she called
the seal of the right eye.
I believe she also said
it was installed.
I did not know
what she meant at the time,
but could this code 8-7-1 seal
be a product of the real world?
Asuna: A seal, 8-7-1.
It must be an inhibitor.
But why would rath
install that in them?
In the end,
it would just get in the way.
Rath's ultimate goal was to make
an a.I. With true intelligence.
The underworld was created
for that purpose,
and that's why kikuoka and Higa
let it evolve
for centuries internally.
If the whole point
of this simulation,
was to give the a.I.S
the opportunity
to demonstrate free will,
forcing them into obedience
with an inhibitor
defeats the purpose.
Unless...
The seal is a kind of sabotage.
Are the people in the ocean
turtle's main con behind this?
No, the saboteur
must be someone with rath.
They could be with us in subcon.
I have to tell kikuoka,
but there's no terminal here.
I could suicide out,
but I need Alice to save Kirito!
What do I do?
Kirito: You know...
What to do.
( Asuna gasps )
( Sighs )
Alice:
Is something wrong with you?
Asuna: No. I'm fine.
Alice is right.
That code 8-7-1 seal
was put there by someone,
someone from my world,
and they're
on the enemy's side.
Bercouli: Hmm.
How do we get rid of the seal?
Is there a way to do it without
blowing out someone's eyeball?
Asuna: I'm sorry,
but I don't know of another way
to disable it
from inside the underworld.
( Bercouli sighs ) All right.
Based on what we know
about this enemy,
they only want someone
who's got the willpower
to break the seal
of the right eye. Why one of us?
Do all the folks in your world
have a seal like we do?
Asuna: No. That's something
we've never had to suffer.
In fact, I believe
the only point of difference
between the underworlders
and the real-worlders
is how you're being forced
to obey your laws and orders.
Whoever's responsible
for the seal in your eye
doesn't want you
having free will.
They're afraid
of this priestess of light,
as you call her,
because someone like that
could ruin
whatever they had planned.
And if she appeared in my world,
your priestess of light would be
considered extremely valuable.
Bercouli: I still don't get
what the fuss is about.
You said so yourself just now.
There ain't a whole lot
of difference between our kinds.
The only thing
is the seal of the right eye.
Except for Alice here.
She broke her seal,
and according to you,
she's no different
than a real-worlder now.
You got a world
full of your kind already,
so why are you
and your enemies
so obsessed
with snatchin' up little Alice?
And once you do
get her in your world,
what are you plannin'
on doin' with her?
Asuna: Sorry.
I can't say, not right now.
She should see
the real world first.
Then she can decide what she
wants to do for herself.
It's not heaven.
It's no paradise, either,
not even close.
Compared to here,
it's not as tranquil.
It's not as pretty or as clean.
But still, there are
good things about my world,
the people, for one.
There's some
who'd want to exploit you,
but there's more who'd want
to protect this world,
just like Kirito.
( Alice gasps )
ｶ
I have questions,
but they can wait until later.
First we must focus
on breaking the enemy army,
and then we must make peace
with the dark territory.
I will not go anywhere
until then.
Asuna: Fine. Besides,
now that we know
vecta's from the real world,
it'd be dangerous for us to
leave the safety of your army.
He'll be expecting that,
I'm sure.
That said, I'll join your people
in the fight.
As for vecta,
let me deal with him.
- ( Captains murmuring )
- Captain: All right!
Bercouli: We're glad
to have you along.
About your skill, how you
split the ground open like that,
is there a limit to using it?
Asuna: There is. I can alter
the landscape like that
one or two more times,
but that's it.
( Captains sigh )
Alice: This is our world,
remember?
Protecting it
is our responsibility, not hers.
Let us show her
what we are capable of!
Renly: Yes. Yes, you are right!
Lady Asuna is not a god.
She just told us she was human,
like the rest of us.
If she is willing to fight hard,
then we shall fight
even harder,
Sheyta: I support this, if only
to fight that pugilist again.
Golgorosso: You're right.
It's our world!
It's our duty to protect it!
( Overlapping chatter )
Asuna: And I'll protect
this world Kirito loved
from the hijackers
aboard the ocean turtle
and from rath, if I have to.
( Insects chirping )
Alice: I knew you would come.
( Asuna gasps )
Alice: Hmph.
( Sighs )
All right,
I will let you see him,
and I will tell you
everything I know of him.
In return, however,
if you are agreeable,
you must tell me
everything you know of him.
( Asuna chuckles )
It's a deal,
but we go back a long way,
so there's a lot to tell.
Just how long
were you and he together?
Asuna: Let's see.
I was his partner in battle
for two years.
Then we dated properly
for a year and a half,
and for two weeks,
we even lived together.
Alice: Is that so?
Well, I fought
by his side for one night,
but for the past six months,
I have lived with him
and taken care of him.
Asuna: Uh, really? That long?
Ronie: Excuse me.
Um, he--he was my mentor,
and I cleaned his room
for two months,
and I also learned
sword skills from him.
He also brought me honey pies
from the prancing deer cafﾉ.
I know I didn't spend as much
time with him as either of you,
but I'd like
to swap stories with you.
- ( Both chuckle )
- Asuna: All right.
You're more than welcome
to join us if you want, Ronie.
( Ronie sighs )
Liena: Pardon me for intruding,
but would you have room
for one more in your group?
Asuna: Hello there.
I saw you at the meeting.
Liena: I am an imperial knight
of norlangarth,
and my name
is sortiliena serlut.
I was going to wait until
after the battle to see him,
but since Kirito and I
share a bit of history,
I was most eager
to see how he was faring.
( Alice sighs )
Understandable,
chief guard serlut.
How do you know Kirito?
Liena: You may call me Liena,
if it pleases you, lady knight.
( Clears throat )
Kirito was a primary trainee
at the north centoria
swordcraft academy,
where I, too, was studying.
For one year,
he served as my page.
We trained together,
and in so doing,
I taught him
some of my sword skills.
Asuna: Uh...
( Alice chuckles )
Asuna: Okay. It already sounds
like you'll have
tons of neat stories.
Welcome to the club, Liena.
( Tent rustles )
ｶ
( chuckles )
Alice: What is it?
Asuna: Back where we come from,
he's called
"dual-wielding Kirito."
Alice: Really?
Perhaps we should start
with you telling us
how he got that name.
( All laugh )
( Alice chuckles )
( Singing in Japanese )
ｶ