¶
( Alice sighs )
Girl: Alice!
( Running footsteps )
Good morning!
- ( Laughs )
- Alice: Selka.
Selka: Hee! ( Sighs )
( Alice chuckles )
Good morning.
What brings you here?
Selka: The weather's so nice.
I thought we could take
a walk to the eastern hill,
you, me, and Kirito of course.
( Alice sighs )
It is a lovely day.
The fresh air would do him good.
( Fire crackling )
Shall we go, then, Kirito?
¶
( singing in Japanese )
¶ no pain, no gain for dream
¶
There.
Let's get going.
Kirito: Ahh. Ahh.
Alice: Oh. I'm sorry.
I'll get them for you.
¶
Be careful with them.
Hold them tight now.
( Dragon snorts )
Alice: I hope he is warm enough.
( Selka groans )
Sometimes you can be
such a worrywart.
You bundled him up so much,
he's sweating.
Aren't you, Kirito?
I know eugeo'd think so.
( Wind blowing )
Alice: How beautiful.
None of the paintings
in the cathedral
can compare with this view.
You saved this world, Kirito.
Remember?
Higa: We're screwed!
What do we do?!
If they cut
the main power line now,
it's gonna cause a surge!
Lightcube clusters
should be safe,
but the subcomputer where
kirigaya's s.T.L. Is won't be!
The surge'll cook
his fluctlight!
( Kikuoka gasps ) O-okay,
I'll handle the lockdown.
Higa, take Dr. Kojiro and Asuna
and get to the upper shaft.
Keep Kirito safe.
- Kirito: Asuna?
- Alice: Kirito?
Security:
They're cutting the power!
The screw propellers
are going down!
( Tone blares )
( Crackling )
¶
Alice: Kirito!
Kirito.
Kirito!
You cannot die,
not after saving my life!
Kirito!
Kirito.
( Crying )
Bercouli: Hey, kid.
Alice: U-uncle.
Bercouli: What happened?
We're facing the biggest crisis
in the history
of the axiom church.
Those two elite disciples
we fought killed the Pontifex.
Fanatio: No! It can't be!
Eldrie: She's dead? Impossible.
Bercouli: That's not all.
Chudelkin died
with the Pontifex.
With him gone,
there's no more senate.
( Knights gasp )
Eldrie: This makes no sense.
Why would those disciples
risk angering the gods
with their actions?
Bercouli: To stop the Pontifex
before she turned
half the human realm
into weapons of war,
an army of mindless,
living swords.
Eldrie: How could she
do such a thing?
To subject the people
to such horror...
Deusolbert: It's diabolical,
eldrie: Sir bercouli,
where are the two rogues
who murdered her eminence?
They must be captured
and interrogated.
Bercouli: We don't have time
to deal with that right now.
The dark territory's
been itching to invade us,
and, when they find out
about the Pontifex, they will.
Our ranks are half as strong,
thanks to past battles
with the forces of darkness.
We should all
be worried about that.
If the dark territory
decides to attack us now,
the human realm
will fall for sure.
Fanatio: Then,
what should we do?
Or, rather, what can we do?
Bercouli: First, we'll restore
the order
of the integrity knights.
Then we'll muster
the imperial knights
of the four empires
and train them for battle.
There's strength in numbers,
and right now we need
all the help we can get.
I know what I told you
is hard to accept,
but it's still our job
to protect the people here.
I can't do that without you.
Knights: Sir!
( Soldiers yelling together )
( Dragon grunts )
( Alice sighs )
I wonder if Kirito's hungry.
Man: There's a rumor
going around,
saying that rebel swordsman
is still alive.
Man 2: I heard.
He's supposed to be in a coma.
Man 1: I know we have to prepare
for the dark territory
to invade,
but leaving
that traitor in our midst?
He defied the church
and should be executed for it.
Man 2: Agreed. Who knows what
commander bercouli is thinking?
¶
Alice: It is no longer safe
for Kirito here.
( Gate grinds )
We shall go to rulid village.
Perhaps they
will accept us there,
since it is the place
where eugeo and I were born.
Zink: Huh? ( Gasps )
Hold on, you!
Strangers aren't allowed in
unless I say so!
( Gasps ) What in the...
( Gasps ) By the gods.
It can't be.
Alice: I am no stranger.
I am Alice.
Summon Gasfut Zuberg at once.
( Villagers murmuring )
( Gasfut gasps )
( Sighs )
¶
is that really you?
Alice?
Alice: Yes.
Gasfut: Well, then,
what are you doing here?
Have you been pardoned
for your crime?
Alice: Perhaps.
I certainly was punished for it.
All of the memories I had
of my life here were wiped away.
If that is not enough
to absolve me,
no one's said otherwise.
Regardless, I have returned,
because I could think
of nowhere else to go.
( Gasfut sighs )
- Begone.
- ( Alice gasps )
Gasfut: We cannot allow
a criminal to stay here.
( Alice sighs )
Selka: What's wrong?
Alice: It is nothing.
Shall we start heading back?
Selka: Sure.
¶
( Selka grunts )
Alice: What is it, selka?
Something troubles you.
Selka: Well,
i-it's nothing serious.
It's Mr. Barbossa.
He asked if you could chop down
another tree for him.
Alice: Honestly?
That's why you're so quiet?
You do know
he and I have an agreement.
Selka: Yes, but how dare he?
The hypocrite,
both him and Mr. Ridack.
They don't hesitate to ask you
for help when they need it,
but they don't mind you
being shunned by the village.
Alice: It's all right, selka.
As long as I can have
a place on the outskirts,
that's enough for me.
Selka: Yes, but next year
my training will be done,
and I was thinking,
since I'll be earning
a little money,
I could give you that.
It's not much, but it's enough
that you won't have to help
those people anymore.
You and Kirito
don't have to worry.
I'll help somehow.
Alice: I'm grateful.
But having you close by
is all I could ever need.
I am happy
just to have that, selka.
( Wind blowing )
( Chopping )
( Woodcutter groans )
Barbossa: Why is
this taking so long?
In the time it takes you
to cut this damn tree down,
ridack's men will have expanded
his land 20 mels in--
Alice: Good day, Mr. Barbossa.
Barbossa: Alice!
How good of you to come,
and so quickly, too.
Alice: I heard
you need my assistance.
Barbossa: Yes.
It's that one over there.
We've been hacking away at it
since yesterday morning.
These damned
platinum oak trees are tough.
Why, ten grown men have put
their backs into every swing,
and they've barely
made a scratch in it,
so I asked for you.
I know our deal
is for one tree a month,
but this one's stubborn,
and I really need
your help here, Alice.
What do you say?
Alice: I shall do it,
and happily.
But just this once, understood?
Barbossa: Great!
I knew I could count on you.
( Scoffs )
¶
Alice: If you don't mind,
Kirito,
I need your sword,
but only for a moment.
( Gasps )
( Sighs )
( Kirito grunts )
Alice: Thank you.
¶
woodcutter: Come on!
You think you're gonna cut down
a platinum oak
with a li'l old sword?
Woodcutter 2:
It'll snap in half.
( Men laughing )
¶
( Alice grunts )
- Huh?
- ( Murmuring )
Woodcutter 2:
Look at that. She missed!
Alice: You'd best
move away from there.
Woodcutter 2: What?
- Why should we--
- ( Tree creaking )
( Both gasping )
( Barbossa gasps )
Splendid!
Wonderful!
Magnificent!
Your skill is unbelievable!
No, exceptional!
Hear me out now.
I shall double
your compensation,
and, instead of once a month,
you'd work for me once a week--
no, once a day!
I know you could use the money.
Alice: Thank you, but the amount
you are paying now
is quite sufficient.
( Barbossa gasps )
( Groans )
Eh?
Alice: My payment.
Barbossa: Oh. Of course!
Yes, right away.
Thank you, Mr. Barbossa.
- ( Thump )
- ( Gasps )
Kirito!
( Barbossa stammers)
( Kirito sighing )
Man: What the--it's so heavy!
Man 2: How else do you think
she cut that tree down?
- Anyone could, with that sword!
- Man 3: Let me try.
( Grunting )
( Alice gasps )
( Men gasp )
Alice: That sword
belongs to Kirito.
Get your hands off it.
( Man 3 growls ) We asked him!
If he didn't
want us touching it,
he should've said something!
Man 1: He's right.
We asked him nicely,
and all he did was go,
"eh eh," like a gibbering fool.
( Men gasp )
Man 3: Fine, take it.
It's just a damn sword.
( Blue Rose sword thumps )
¶
Alice: Is this what
we fought for, suffered for,
to protect people like these?
Eugeo lost his life.
Kirito is a shell
of his former self.
If there was a point
to all we've been through,
it is lost to me.
( Dragon growls )
( Snorts )
Amayori. It seems
you've gained some weight.
You've been gorging
on too many fish.
( Footsteps rumbling )
( Amayori groans )
Alice: Good night. Sleep well.
( Blowing )
Here.
Don't eat too fast now.
( Amayori growling )
( Alice gasps )
Is that...
( Dragon grunts )
( Amayori trills )
Alice: Takiguri,
amayori's elder brother.
Which means...
I'm impressed you found us.
Now, why have you come,
eldrie synthesis thirty-one?
Eldrie: It has been
far too long,
my lady, my mentor.
Alice: So how did you find me?
More importantly, why?
I am sure the order
has better things to do now
than send dragons all over
just to track me down.
Eldrie: You won't believe this,
but I simply followed
the bond between our souls.
Hah! If only that were true.
No, I found you
by complete coincidence.
Although, now that I am here,
I have news.
The goblins and orcs have
been mobilizing in the north.
- ( Alice gasps )
- Eldrie: As for why I'm here,
the commander ordered us
to collapse the caves
to the south and west,
and, here in the north,
I was sent to make sure
the fiends hadn't dug them out.
Alice: And? Is the cave
north of here safe,
or have they dug through it?
Eldrie: I spent
all day up there,
keeping a vigilant eye upon it.
In all that time, I did not
spot any orcs or goblins.
I'm happy to report the cave
is still filled with debris.
Then, as I made my way
back to the capital,
takiguri began
behaving strangely.
I allowed him free rein,
and this is
where he chose to land...
Your new home.
And, now that we've
been reunited at last,
you will forgive me
for speaking my mind.
Lady Alice...
Please return to the order!
We need your sword now
more than ever,
more than an army of thousands!
Alice: I cannot.
Eldrie: Why not?!
( Grunts )
Is it because of that one?
The man who escaped from prison,
the man who flouted the law,
who raised his sword
against your fellow knights,
the prime senator,
and the Pontifex?
Is he still
leading your heart astray?
If so, there is but one solution
for your confusion.
I shall eliminate him at once!
- Alice: Stop it.
- ( Eldrie gasps )
Alice: He fought
not for himself,
but for what
he believed was right,
for justice.
Is that not
what the knighthood fights for?
He defeated us
one after the other,
including the commander.
When you fought him,
surely you could feel
the purity of his conviction
in the weight of his sword.
Eldrie: If he is
as pure as you say,
then why won't he take up
his sword and help us now?
How could he allow himself
to be reduced
to such a pathetic state
and shackle you
to these hinterlands?
If what I heard is true
and he killed the Pontifex
for the sake of the people,
then it is his duty
to join them at the eastern gate
and defend the land!
Alice: Forgive me, eldrie,
but I cannot go with you
to assist in the battle.
It has nothing to do with him.
I can no longer wield my sword.
That is the reason.
If you and I crossed swords now,
I doubt I would last
three strikes.
Eldrie: Is that so?
All right.
I will not press you further.
I bid you farewell, milady.
You were my mentor,
and, as long as I live,
I shall never forget
all you have taught me.
Alice: Farewell, then.
I pray you'll be safe.
( Eldrie grunts )
( Amayori trills )
( Takiguri warbles )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Alice: It's gotten late.
You must be tired.
Let's get you to bed, shall we?
( Singing in Japanese )
( Kirito breathing )
Alice: Tell me, Kirito.
( Shudders )
What should I do?
( Singing in Japanese )
Alice: What should I do?
( Kirito gasping )
Alice: Kirito?
Alice: What is it? What's wrong?
- ( Amayori growls )
- ( Alice gasps )
( Singing in Japanese )
( Alice gasps )
A fire. ( Gasps )
The dark territory is attacking!
( Sighs )
Selka!