ｶ
( Soldiers grunting )
Eldrie: Hmm.
( Takiguri trilling )
Eldrie: Is that...
( Takiguri trills )
- Eldrie: Milady!
- ( Alice gasps )
Eldrie: I knew
you'd return to help!
( Gasps )
( Grunts )
Milady.
ｶ
( singing in Japanese )
Alice: I have just returned
from the eastern gate.
There is not much time
before it crumbles away
and the army of the dark
marches through.
Eldrie: They have 50,000.
We have but 3,000.
As far as training them,
we are doing all we can.
Alice: And where
are the other integrity knights?
Are they all out on patrol?
As I made my approach,
I could only see seven.
Eldrie: They are
all we have here.
Alice: What? That is impossible!
Counting the two of us,
there should be
31 knights in the order!
Technically, there are, milady.
But you know as well as I,
when a knight
showed signs of distress,
chudelkin would use the arts
to recalibrate them.
At the last count,
ten knights have yet
to be awakened from that.
( Alice gasps )
Eldrie: Currently,
21 knights are active.
There are four
stationed at the cathedral
to guard the capitol,
and four are on patrol
over the end mountains.
Alice: That only
leaves 13 then.
Eldrie: Needless to say,
we are stretched far too thin.
And with all that we face...
( Sighs ) You brought him.
Do you intend to protect him
while you fight?
Alice: Yes, of course.
I've sworn to protect him.
Eldrie: But how can you?!
He is nothing but dead weight!
If you burden yourself with him,
not only will it affect
your ability to fight,
it'll place you
in certain danger!
( Grunts )
Bercouli: That's enough, Eldrie.
Relax.
Hey, little girl!
You look like you been
taking care of yourself.
Even your cheeks filled in.
Alice: Hello, uncle.
It has been too long.
( Bercouli chuckles )
Eldrie: Commander--( Gasps )
ｶ
Alice: What's wrong? ( Gasps )
( Thinking )
Is he going to kill Kirito?
Bercouli: No need for that, kid.
( Alice gasps )
( Bercouli breathes deeply )
- ( Grunts )
- ( Metal rings )
Alice: U-uncle.
Bercouli: All right,
tell me what you saw.
Alice: I think I saw...
A flash of swords just now.
Bercouli: Mm-hmm. I tossed
an incarnate sword at him.
Well, actually it was
more like a dagger.
It only would have
scratched his cheek a bit,
if it hit him, that is.
Alice: "If it hit"?
Then that means he--
Bercouli: That's right.
He stopped it.
He did it with his willpower.
( Alice gasps )
Bercouli: It might not look
like his mind's all there,
but the kid ain't dead. No way.
And he wasn't protecting himself
when he blocked my strike.
- He was protecting you.
- ( Alice gasps )
Bercouli: He'll snap
out of it one day.
That's what I think.
I can't tell you when,
but I bet it'll be
when you need him the most.
( Alice grunts )
( Sighs )
Bercouli: Don't get hung up
on the small stuff, Eldrie.
We can look after
this kid, easy.
( Eldrie grunts )
( Kirito grunting )
Alice: Right.
I shall get them.
( Kirito sighing )
Alice: Kirito.
Even though the battle
with administrator
cost you your heart,
still, you had the will
to protect me
from uncle's sword technique.
Tell me,
what do you think of me?
And to that end,
what do I think of you?
Ridiculous.
I am unnatural,
a puppet created to fight
using Alice zuberg's body
as a vessel.
I am not allowed
the luxury of emotions,
only the will to do battle.
Although, what if...
That is why I cannot
break through to you,
because I hold myself back?
Would you respond if I unleashed
all of my will right now?
( Bell jingles )
( Gasps )
( Bells jingle )
Tiese: U-um...
We--we brought some supper
for you, milady.
Alice: Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Ronie: Oh, and here is
your bread and drink.
Alice: There is nothing
to be afraid of.
I see by your uniforms
you are
from the swordcraft academy.
Tiese: Yes, my lady, we are.
I'm primary trainee
Tiese Schtrinen,
army supply corps,
at your service.
Ronie: And I'm primary trainee
Ronie Arabel, ma'am!
Alice: You do not have
to be so formal with me.
I am a warrior, here to protect
the land, same as you,
so please call me Alice.
( Gasps )
What is wrong?
Tiese: Huh? No, nothing!
It's just that when we first
met you at the academy,
you seemed different
than you are now.
Alice: Oh. Was I?
Anyway, is there
something I can do for you?
Tiese: Yes, I think.
( Both grunt )
Tiese: Um, sorry to pry, Mila--
I mean, Alice,
but the word around the camp
is that you came here
with a black-haired boy.
Ronie: We knew someone
at the academy like that,
and we thought
we'd come see if it was him,
if you don't mind.
Alice: No,
of course I do not mind.
Now that I recall,
you were friends of Kirito's
at the academy.
Ronie: I knew it! It is Kirito!
Tiese: Then Eugeo
must be here, too! Yeah!
- Alice: I am sorry.
- Both: Huh?
Alice: There is
no easy way to say this.
I do not wish to upset you.
However, since Eugeo and Kirito
were your mentors,
you have the right to know.
( Bells jingle )
( Both gasp )
ｶ
( Both crying )
( Tiese gasps )
Just now, I heard him.
It was Eugeo.
He said not to cry
and he'll be here, always.
( Crying )
ｶ
Alice: I am sorry.
You must love them dearly.
Ronie: Don't say that!
We--we could never...
Tiese: Lady Alice, when you
arrested Kirito and Eugeo,
did you know what they did?
Alice: Yes. They violated
one of the taboos.
They were involved
in the death of another.
Tiese: And do you know what led
up to them breaking that taboo?
Alice: No, not entirely.
Tiese: They raised their swords
to save us,
because we weren't strong enough
to save ourselves.
( Alice gasps )
Tiese: If only we'd handled
our troubles ourselves,
they wouldn't have rebelled
against the laws of the church,
and no one would have died.
Ultimately, we are the ones
to blame for what happened.
That's why...
No matter how we
truly feel about them...
We can't say we love them!
Alice: It is not your fault.
You've done nothing wrong.
Ronie: But we have!
You're a noble integrity knight,
so you can't understand!
We're sinners!
We caused bloodshed
by letting ourselves be defiled!
Alice: The body
is nothing more than a vessel.
Your heart, your soul
is who you really are,
and you determine
the nature of your soul,
you, and you alone.
( Thinking ) Show them...
ｶ
Just like Kirito showed you.
( Both gasp )
ｶ
Alice: You see?
The person you really are
is but the reflection
of your heart,
and that cannot be defiled.
I was born in a tiny village.
I should have grown up
to become who you see now,
but when I was just a child,
I was arrested for a crime.
My memories were erased,
and I was turned into
an integrity knight.
There were times
I cursed my fate.
However, Kirito taught me
to overcome it,
that I had the power to.
I just had to will it,
and I won't doubt myself again.
I've chosen to accept who I am
and move on.
I am sure, given time,
the two of you will also
find your way and find peace.
( Both crying )
Birds chirping )
Bercouli: Hey.
Alice: Uncle.
- Good morning.
- ( Bercouli grunts )
I was thinking
about your friend just now
and what to do with him
when the fighting starts.
Alice: I have already
made arrangements.
Last night, I was paid a visit
by his former pages
from the academy.
I trust them, so I asked them
to look after Kirito.
Bercouli: Good.
Glad that's settled.
By the way,
how'd the kid take it?
Did seeing
these folks from his past
snap him out of his fog any?
Alice: Mm-mmm.
Bercouli: Oh, well. Chin up.
Something tells me he'll
come around and, when he does,
he'll be the one
who sets the course of this war.
- Alice: Hmm?
- Bercouli: Even if he got help
from you and his partner,
killing the prime senator
and the pontifex
was anything but easy.
If I took him on,
I doubt I'd last
against his incarnate ability.
( Alice gasps )
You exaggerate.
Bercouli: Yesterday,
when our wills clashed,
I definitely felt it.
That kid's got equal
or, hell, even more experience
in real combat than me.
Alice: But how is that possible?
You are much older.
Bercouli: Not in experience.
- He's got way more.
- ( Alice gasps )
Bercouli: The taboo index
forbids battles to the death,
but he's got
tons of experience with that.
Question is, how?
Alice: Uncle, he is not from--
Fanatio: Commander.
It is time for the council.
Alice: Lady Fanatio.
( Gasps )
ｶ
( thinking )
Sh-she is wearing makeup?
Fanatio: It has
been ages, Alice.
You've been well, I take it?
Alice: So feminine!
Y-Yes, and you?
Fanatio: As well as can be.
Say, is it true you brought
that black-haired boy here?
- Alice: I have.
- Fanatio: Good.
After our meeting, I would
like to see him for a moment.
Alice: For what reason?
Fanatio: I wish to thank him.
It won't take long.
Alice: Thank him?
Fanatio: Indeed.
Even though he defeated me,
he fought honorably.
Truth be told,
that boy is the only male
who fought me with all he had.
It did not matter to him
in the slightest
that I happened to be a woman.
Alice: Why would that matter?
Fanatio: When I first became
a knight and fought with men,
I could tell they held back,
so I donned this helmet
and mastered the art
of continuous attacks
to prevent my opponents
from getting too close.
Ultimately the real issue
was that I was self-conscious
about my gender.
He saw right through me, though,
and fought with all his might,
regardless.
I unleashed all
of my sword techniques and arts,
and he still bested me.
Then after I healed,
my petty obsession
had disappeared entirely.
There! Now do you understand
why I am so eager to thank him?
I am also a tad vexed,
to be honest.
My femininity did not register
with him at all
once he saw my face.
I thought if I saw him,
I could...
Try a few things that
might stimulate his recovery.
( Alice gasps )
I am grateful for your concern,
but he is resting
at the moment.
I will make sure
to give him your regards
- when I check on him later.
- Fanatio: Oh.
It seems you've installed
yourself as his guardian.
Well, whenever
the commander was on duty
and you wished
to speak with him,
I never refused you,
not even once.
Alice: I do not
need your permission.
I can see him any time I choose.
And another thing,
if you truly wished to be
beaten senseless by a male,
surely uncle here
could have obliged you.
Fanatio: I would
not expect him to.
He is the strongest swordsman
in the land.
He would not spar
with his knights full-bore.
- ( Bercouli groans )
- Alice: Oh, you don't say?
Well, whenever I
trained with him,
he was always drenched in sweat
from the exertion.
( Fanatio laughs )
- Is what she says true...
- Alice: Uncle...
- Fanatio: Command--
- Alice: Set this woman strai--
Bercouli: Come on!
It's time
we got this meeting started.
( Both gasp )
( Both sigh )
Fanatio: We have considered
many different strategies
over the past four months
and have concluded that,
at our current strength,
it would be difficult
to repel an all-out attack.
On our side
of the end mountains,
there is nothing
but grassland and rocks
for ten kilors
in all directions.
If the enemy
advances this far,
we will be surrounded
and slaughtered.
Our only option is to engage
them in this narrow ravine,
which is one hundred mels wide
and one thousand mels long.
We will set up
a defensive position here,
absorb their charge,
and grind them down.
This will be the basic thrust
of our strategy.
Does anyone have
any thoughts so far?
Eldrie: I have a concern.
The enemy
has ogres and longbows
and, even more dangerous,
dark mages of untold numbers.
How can we counteract
their long-range attacks?
Fanatio: I have an idea on that.
( Alice gasps )
Fanatio: There is
no sunlight in that ravine,
even during the day.
Not even the grass grows.
Sacred power
is sparse there, at best.
But in theory,
if we absorb the power
from the battlefield first,
their mages won't be able
to use it to attack us.
( Officers gasp )
Fanatio: The same is true
for our side as well.
At the present, we only have
100 who can wield the arts.
If we allow the battle to come
down to our wielders and theirs,
theirs will use far more power.
Deusolbert: The arts are not
just used for combat, though.
If all the sacred power
is exhausted,
healing the lives
of our critically wounded
will be next to impossible.
Fanatio: I admit
it is a risky gamble,
which is why we brought
all the reagents
and healing potions
from the capital.
If we use our sacred arts
only for healing
and the potions for support,
the reagents should last
for at least three days.
Alice: There is one more issue.
If I may...
While solus and terraria's
blessings are sparse there,
during the battle,
with each warrior who falls,
more sacred power
will be released and accumulate.
I do not see how we can absorb
all those extra resources
if there are not
enough of us to do so.
Fanatio: We can.
Well, actually, one of us can.
Alice: Who?
Fanatio: Why, you,
Alice synthesis thirty.
( Alice gasps )
Fanatio: Perhaps you
haven't realized it yet,
but your power
has surpassed that
of all the integrity knights
in the land,
and you are ready to use it now,
a godlike power
that can split heaven and earth.
( Alice grunts )
Would you please
look after Kirito
and keep him safe?
Tiese: Yes. You can count on us.
Ronie: Lady Alice,
don't you worry.
We promise we will
protect him with our lives.
( Alice chuckles )
Kirito, I must leave,
and I do not know
if I shall return.
You saved my life,
and I will use all of it,
to the last drop if I have to.
And so, should I fall in battle
and call you
with the last of my breath,
would you stand
and draw your sword for me?
With you awake,
it would not matter
how many thousands
the enemy has.
You will perform another miracle
and protect everyone,
as before.
After all, you were the one
who defeated administrator.
You are
the greatest swordsman ever.
( Footsteps approach )
Eldrie: Lady Alice.
Are you ready to go?
Alice: Eldrie?
Eldrie: Yes? Milady?
Alice: Thank you.
You have served me well.
( Eldrie gasps )
Alice: I was blessed
to have you by my side,
even though
it was not for long.
You chose an amateur like me
to be your mentor
instead of a male veteran
like sir deusolbert.
Was that out of sympathy for me?
Eldrie: No, not at all!
I would never be
so disrespectful!
I chose you
because I was so in awe
of your sword technique
and skills as a warrior!
Alice: And it is due
to your unwavering support
that I was able to survive
to see this day.
I thank you.
ｶ
Eldrie: Lady Alice,
you speak with such finality.
It is as if you think
your journey,
instead of going on,
is about to end.
It cannot! I still have
not learned all I can from you!
My technique, my arts,
I am nowhere near ready!
I still need you
to continue my training and--
and guide me
to be a better knight!
Alice: Integrity knight
Eldrie synthesis thirty-one!
( Eldrie gasps ) Yes, milady.
Alice: As your mentor,
here are my final orders.
You will survive,
survive to witness
peace in the land,
and after, you will
seek out your true life
and take it back
and the one you love.
( Eldrie shudders )
ｶ
( singing in Japanese )
( Goblin growls )
( Roars )
ｶ
( Iskahn chuckles )
( Knight shudders )
ｶ
( Soldiers gasp )