[RIKKA] I've been
looking all over for you.
Don't follow me.
[ALEXIS]
Hurry it up, Akane.
[AKANE] I told you I can't
make kaiju anymore.
[ALEXIS] I'm fine with you
becoming a kaiju yourself.
Instance Abreaction!
--[AKANE screams]
--[RIKKA gasps]
[AKANE roars]
Akane!
[ALL]
Grid... Full Power... Finish!
[KAIJU A groans]
[ANTI]
Night Light... Wave Missile!
[YUTA]
Thank you.
Without your help,
we couldn't have won.
At the end of my life, I swear
I'm going to defeat you.
Keep living until then.
Right.
You are our Hibiki,
aren't you?
[YUTA]
Yes, but the thing is,
I am also the Hyper
Agent Gridman now.
Hyper Agent, uh... Okay, then.
If all of us combine,
and reunite Gridman's
split consciousness,
Yuta will most
likely awaken. But...
We can't allow Alexis
Kerib to run amok.
And that means we're going
to need everyone's power.
[BORR]
Everyone, huh?
Problem is Utsumi and
Rikka aren't here.
--[beeping]
-[ALL] Huh?
[AKANE roars]
[YUTA]
That kaiju. Shinjo is up to you.
[ANTI]
And you?
[YUTA]
I have something I must do.
Alright then. I pay my debts.
[YUTA grunts]
--[AKANE roars]
--[ANTI] You are not a kaiju.
You're Akane Shinjo!
[ANTI shouts]
[AKANE growls]
[ALEXIS] A human that makes
kaiju is a kaiju herself.
[RIKKA gasps]
[ALEXIS]
Well if isn't--
Sorry, remind me
who you are again.
I'm a friend of Akane Shinjo.
[ALEXIS]
A friend, you say?
[ALEXIS laughs]
Now, wouldn't that be nice?
You're a counterfeit born
from Akane's kaiju.
A fabricated meat-thing.
A replica.
You're a creation that Akane
made for her own benefit.
A creation that thinks
of itself as human.
A creation that believes
its god is a friend.
How sad that is.
[RIKKA] Whether it's sad or
not is up to us to decide.
[ALEXIS] What do you
think as her friend?
Of this world-- No.
Of the downfall of this
cramped city's god.
It's you who made
Akane this way.
[ALEXIS] She's been like that
since the very beginning.
Nothing has changed.
That's why it's so great.
[RIKKA] In that case,
we'll change Akane.
[ALEXIS] At this point?
Mm-hm-hm. Try if you wish.
[gasps]
[RIKKA]
Hibiki!
[ALEXIS]
Long time no see.
Glad you're doing well,
Yuta Hibiki.
Sorry, but from now on,
call me Gridman.
Let's go, Rikka!
Everyone's waiting!
[RIKKA grunts]
[ALEXIS]
Hmph.
[ANTI shouts]
[ANTI]
Akane Shinjo!
[AKANE roars]
[ANTI yells]
[ALL gasp]
Best of luck, Anti.
[footsteps]
[YUTA]
Utsumi!
Hey, Yuta. Oh, wait.
It's Gridman now, isn't it?
[YUTA] It's both.
Please come with me.
[UTSUMI]
No.
[YUTA]
Huh?
[UTSUMI]
I'm not like everyone else.
I'm just a useless
normal person.
[footsteps]
[RIKKA] So what,
because you're "normal",
you're not gonna help anymore?
What happened to all of your
Gridman Allinace talk, huh?
I wasn't even the one
out there fighting,
and Junk belongs
to your family.
[RIKKA gasps]
Utsumi. Junk needs every
one of us to be there.
[UTSUMI sighs]
--[RIKKA] Hey!
--[UTSUMI grunts]
Listen here. Just what are
you to Hibiki anyway?
[UTSUMI grunts]
What am I to him?
[UTSUMI]
I... Well, I'm... Yuta's friend!
Well, that friend is asking
you to help him right now.
[UTSUMI grunts]
[AKANE]
No... No... No... No... No...
[gasps]
[ANTI shouts]
[AKANE]
Why did it have to be you?
You know, you really
are a failed creation.
Yeah. I am the failed
creation that you made.
[ANTI groans]
[gasps]
[ALEXIS]
I'm sorry it took so long.
Finally disposed of him.
Well, I'll have you prove
useful one last time.
[ALEXIS shouts, laughs]
[ALEXIS]
Magnificent!
You said you couldn't
make kaiju anymore!
And yet, here you had such
terrible emotions inside of you!
[ALEXIS]
Now then...
[ALEXIS] There's nothing
of value here anymore.
[footsteps]
[MAX]
We're all here.
[ALL]
Hm?
Okay? The heck's this?
You've all got
an Accepter now!
Accepters join separate
hearts and make them one.
Let's go! Together!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Good luck.
[ALL]
Access... Flash!
[ANTI]
Access... Flash...
[GRIDMAN] Enter the battle code!
The access code is...
Enter Gridman.
[RIKKA gasps]
[RIKKA]
That access code was...
[UTSUMI]
This is the true Access Flash!
This is the form of
the true Gridman!
[NAMIKO] That's the big
guy from yesterday!
[HASS]
"Yesterday".
No... For a long time now.
[ALEXIS] What a nostalgic
look that is, Gridman.
But it doesn't matter.
I will defeat you and
search for the next Akane.
[GRIDMAN] There won't be a next!
It all ends here, Alexis Kerib!
[GRIDMAN, ALEXIS grunting]
[GRIDMAN]
Spark Beam!
[ALEXIS groans]
[GRIDMAN, ALEXIS grunting]
[GRIDMAN]
Neo Superconductive Kick!
[ALEXIS groans]
[GRIDMAN gasps]
[ALEXIS laughs]
What the heck? He's immortal?
[RIKKA gasps]
[GRIDMAN]
Gridknight Saber!
What?
[ALEXIS]
My life is endless and infinite.
But that leaves me with
a deep emptiness inside.
Which is why the only thing
that satisfies my heart
are the emotions of
people like Akane.
[GRIDMAN] Is that why you
got your claws into her?
[ALEXIS laughs]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[ALEXIS shouts]
[GRIDMAN shouts]
[ALEXIS] No, no. In reality, she
was the one who sought out me.
Akane. Is she in there?
[ALEXIS] There was nothing
in this world to begin with.
However, providing kaiju allowed
Akane to build her ideal city.
And destroy it again.
[GRIDMAN]
Destroy her ideal city?
[ALEXIS] She couldn't
control every irregularity,
nor all the lives
that were born here.
Which is exactly why
she needed kaiju.
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[ALEXIS] Meanwhile, I wished
to appease my heart
by allowing it all to
repeat on an infinite loop.
[GRIDMAN]
For such a selfish reason?
[GRIDMAN shouts]
[ALEXIS]
But now,
Akane has reached the
end of her usefulness.
There's nothing left
for me in this world.
[UTSUMI]
He's getting away!
[RIKKA]
Akane!
[ALEXIS]
You, whose life is limited,
cannot hope to defeat me,
a being with lives unlimited!
[GRIDMAN]
That cannot be called a life!
[ALEXIS]
In that case,
I'll just have to deliver your
inevitable end right now,
Gridman!
[GRIDMAN]
Grid... Beam!
[GRIDMAN shouts]
[GRIDMAN]
I see.
My power, is not just the
power to fight and destroy.
[GRIDMAN]
My true power is...
[ALEXIS]
Hmm?
[GRIDMAN]
Grid... Fixer Beam!
[ALEXIS yells]
[ALEXIS] Fixer Beam?
What is this power?
[GRIDMAN] Fixer Beam is the
power to mend this world!
For this world's creator.
To rescue the heart
of Akane Shinjo!
[UTSUMI]
Shinjo.
[YUTA]
Shinjo?
[UTSUMI]
Shinjo!
[YUTA]
[RIKKA]
Akane.
[AKANE]
I can't...
I'm terrible.
It's okay.
You're not alone, Akane.
There isn't anyone
who's perfect.
That's why we rely on others.
If you learn to depend
on someone else,
this city will grow and grow.
And not just this city, the
whole world you made will also.
I can't! A big world's too
much for me to handle!
[RIKKA] That's why we
want you to rely on us.
To believe us. That's what
our relationship is.
[AKANE]
Our relationship?
You're all... my...
You're my friends.
This is a world that I created.
Which is why I can't be here.
I have to leave by
my own free will!
To where... I belong.
[ALEXIS yells]
[ALEXIS]
It can't be!
To think you really
mended Akane's heart?
[GRIDMAN]
And that's not all!
Humans have the
power of potential!
Which I-- Which we believe in!
[ALEXIS]
What kind of power is that?!
[GRIDMAN]
This is the power of mortality!
[ALEXIS yells]
[ALEXIS groans]
[ALEXIS] This is the power
of a life which is finite?
You're leaving then?
I did a lot here. Lots of
things that can never be undone.
I know.
I was afraid. I'm such a coward.
Not only that, I'm a wimp.
I was unfair. So weak.
I said I know.
I know all of the things
that you are, Akane.
[AKANE]
I'm so sorry.
I really am... so sorry.
[RIKKA]
Open it.
[AKANE] A pass holder.
You're telling me to "get lost"?
Not even close.
With this, wherever you go,
you'll be like me.
Promise me. Wherever you go,
you'll make an impression.
Because, don't forget,
you're our god.
[AKANE]
Mm. I will.
One last thing, God.
Would it be okay if I
asked for a request?
[AKANE]
Mm-hm.
I want the two of
us to be together.
Let's hope that my wish...
never comes true.
Wasn't there something important
you wanted to tell Shinjo?
So much I could die!
Thing is, I can't
get there after all.
[YUTA chuckles]
[RIKKA] It's not that
big of a deal, y'know.
Though, we won't be in the
same class as a god anymore.
Somewhere out there's a world
the gods call their own.
Gridman has one too, right?
A world like that?
[YUTA]
Mm-hm.
Once you make it
back to your home,
tell everyone
about my exploits.
[YUTA]
Mm.
And if you come back here,
Dwell in me and not Yuta.
That way, I can avoid
another sad goodbye.
Alright, sure. The real Yuta
will awaken after this,
so take care of him for me.
But when he does, do you think
Hibiki will even remember us?
Hey, don't worry.
You can just become friends
with him all over again.
[GRIDMAN]
Even if he doesn't remember,
it's all engraved in the heart.
Just like his feelings for
you came through,
even as I dwelled inside.
Feelings for me?
[GRIDMAN] As a Hyper Agent,
I am grateful for all your help.
Alexis Kerib is sealed.
Now we must return
to the Hyper World.
Our mission is complete.
Thank you. You all
fought so bravely.
It was Rikka's bold actions that
saved us time and time again.
And even though Utsumi
was constantly leading us
down the wrong path with
his worthless predictions...
[BORR chuckles]
...it was still a lot of fun.
You aren't alone.
Nor Akane Shinjo.
[GRIDMAN]
If not for all of you,
our mission may not
have succeeded.
Thank you.
I learned again the importance
of having friends I can trust.
And I learned it from you.
But we should be the
ones thanking you.
So thank you, Gridman.
Thank you, Gridman.
[GRIDMAN]
Well then, take care.
[RIKKA]
Goodbye.
[UTSUMI]
[gasps]
Wait, what about Anti?
He's not coming with us.
Can't pay back the debt.
[gasps]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[FEMALE TRACK STUDENT A]
Tsurumoto, you've got this!
[FEMALE TRACK STUDENT B]
Keep it up!
[NAMIKO]
Huh? Seriously?
[UTSUMI] I wonder why Gridman
picked Yuta to dwell in?
Well, Hibiki was in the
seat next to Akane, so...
Do you think that's
the only reason?
[RIKKA]
I'm sure that's not all of it.
[sneezes] No wonder it's
coming down. It's freezing.
[RIKKA]
Snow.
[ANTI gasps]
[ANTI]
Who the hell are you?
Oh, me? I happen to be the
one who saved your life.
Are you a kaiju?
[ANOSILLUS]
You too, right?
[ANTI]
Yeah, but... I pay my debts.
[laughs]
[ANOSILLUS]
Just like my family does.
[KAIJU B roars]