♪
[STUDENTS chatter]
[FACULTY A] Students.
May I have your attention?
Would Kousaku Sakamoto from
class Three-C come to the
staff room immediately?
[UTSUMI] You're saying
Akane Shinjo's a god?
[RIKKA] Sorry, but you're
not making any sense.
I mean it's not like I
believed it at first either,
but that's what
the girl told me.
What girl is this?
Well, she's about as tall
as a middle schooler,
except she's actually a kaiju.
I'm gonna smack you now.
No! I'm serious!
I'm telling you! It's the truth!
Your story is disgusting.
[UTSUMI]
So disgusting.
She's uses kaiju for two
express purposes.
To destroy the city.
And to fix the city.
She's done this
many times already.
I told you, outside the
city there's nothing.
You really expect us to believe
there's nothing
outside the city?
I know it's crazy, but--
Just listen to yourself.
You're actually buying into
everything this so-called
kaiju girl said?
[YUTA grunts]
To recap. Akane's the one
who's making the kaiju,
which destroy and fix the city?
Yes! Look up!
The ones that never attack
probably do the repairs!
[UTSUMI] Okay, but what does
that have to do with Shinjo?
There's no connection.
[YUTA]
Well, what if...
I dunno, Shinjo's into
kaiju or something?
You've got to be kidding me.
That's the last thing a girl
in high school would like.
Yeah, right. No way.
Wait 'til you hear this!
You know the blue kaiju
that always appears?
[ALL gasp]
Yeah, so uh. I'm kinda giving
a school tour right now.
--[YUTA] Sorry.
--[RIKKA] We're sorry.
Keep it down.
[school bell rings]
[RIKKA]
Shoot! There's the bell!
[UTSUMI] For crying out loud.
Think he's mad at us?
[YUTA] Guys! Would you
just listen to me?
[TEACHER A] Can anyone
tell me what that means?
If you can't discover your
own identity, then it becomes
impossible for you to describe
yourself as an individual.
For example...
[AKANE]
Huh? What is it?
Wha--? Oh, um, nothing.
[STUDENTS chatter]
[YUTA]
It's no use.
The idea's so far out there,
I can't even ask her.
So what now?
What do I do?
[gasps]
Oh, crap! What're you doing
here at my school?
Don't run!
[STUDENTS shouting]
[YUTA, ANTI pant]
I don't care about you!
Bring out Gridman!
That's the thing!
The only time he appears,
is when a kaiju shows up!
He needs a kaiju in
order to show up?
[YUTA]
Shoot! Why'd I say that?
What happens if he decides
to transform right here?
[ANTI grunts]
[gasps]
He ran away?
[ANTI grunts]
[YUTA gasps]
That was strange.
So what is he after?
[AKANE] You mind telling me why
you decided to come by here?
[ANTI]
I want to crush Gridman.
And once he shows up,
I can transform into
a kaiju on my own will.
Was that how that whole
thing was set up?
I honestly can't remember.
So give me the order to
crush him right now!
That way, Gridman will
appear and I--
Keep your voice down.
We are at school, you know.
[AKANE]
Don't do anything stupid again.
[ALEXIS]
Hmm...
[YUTA] So um, you see, whenever
she views something as being
imperfect with the world
and wants to get rid of it,
she'll somehow
make a kaiju which--
Which then destroys the
city before resetting it.
[RIKKA] Yeah. Says the girl
who's also a kaiju. We got it.
[YUTA]
Sounds too far-fetched?
[RIKKA] You have to ask?
For starters--
[MAX] No. Whoever she was,
I saw her too.
Yuta is not lying to you.
Though she did seem
rather mysterious.
[UTSUMI, RIKKA]
Huh?
[YUTA]
What do you think?
I... I think nothing.
[YUTA groans]
[MAX] If she is in your class,
just ask her directly.
I tried doing that today,
but it didn't go very well.
Why don't you ask her instead?
You really think I'm gonna
bring up that ridiculous story?
I nominate you to ask, Utsumi.
Gimme a break, no thank you.
What are your thoughts
about all this, Gridman?
[GRIDMAN]
Sorry, but I don't know either.
[YUTA] You don't
remember any kaiju girl?
[GRIDMAN] I'm afraid I have
no information regarding her.
[YUTA]
I see.
G-Gridman is incomplete.
He needs more time.
Not that the rest of us really
have any room to talk.
Well, then it's settled.
I'll ask Shinjo tomorrow.
[GRIDMAN] Kaiju born
from a person's heart.
That's what the girl
from the train said.
Something about how Shinjo's
heart is what brings them
into the world!
Akane's heart. Meaning what?
Is that sort of
thing even possible?
If we're thinking about
the Ultra series,
it would totally be plausible.
[UTSUMI]
U-Uh, just talking to myself!
[YUTA]
If only I could meet her again.
Maybe then I'd understand
what's going on.
[YUTA]
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow I'll ask
Shinjo and find out.
[YUTA gasps]
Wh-Why are you here? Shinjo?
Welcome home, Mr. Gridman.
How'd you get
inside my apartment?
You found a key?
[AKANE] Hey, you have anything
to drink? I'm so thirty.
[YUTA]
Just tea.
[YUTA gulps]
I'll turn on the air.
[sighs] There's no need
to bother. After all, I am...
You're a god. Is that right?
Huh? So you knew!
That'll make things easy then.
[AKANE sniffs]
This pillow smells like Hibiki.
[AKANE]
Hey, you wanna join me?
Huh?
[AKANE] Stop pretending
like you don't know.
I'm saying we should
join forces.
Become my ally.
You'd have a lot
of fun with a god.
You can do whatever you want.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
[grunts]
[YUTA] I'm sorry,
but I can't join you.
[AKANE]
Why not?
[YUTA] Because. I have
something I must do.
I have very close friends
who live in this city.
And I can't betray them.
What do you mean?
Are you saying I'm
not your friend?
The thing is...
[sighs]
[YUTA gasps]
Hey, walk me back home.
It's getting late outside.
[AKANE] This city's so
jam-packed with useless things.
[YUTA]
Really?
[AKANE]
Really.
[YUTA] So you use kaiju to
destroy the useless things.
The things you don't like,
and then rebuild.
You're really the
one doing that?
Oh, so you know about
the repairs, too!
Gridman's on the ball.
How are you making the kaiju?
Is it actually true that they're
somehow born from your heart?
Wouldn't you like to know!
Hi. Yeah, of course it's me.
So, hey. Listen.
Could you come meet us?
There's somebody I want
to introduce you to.
Huh?
You haven't eaten, right?
My friend says dinner's on them.
[music softly plays]
[RIKKA]
Next time, I'll give it to her.
Hm?
Hello?
[HASS, NAMIKO]
Rikka!
What's up, guys?
[HASS] Tomorrow we hand in
our literature notes, right?
Yeah, that's right. I'm guessing
you want to copy mine?
[HASS] Oh! Spot on, Rikka!
You're the best!
[NAMIKO] You're a god
disguised as a high schooler!
Yeah, whatever. So, where is
it you wanna meet up?
[YUTA]
This is...
Let's go.
[TONKAWA'S DAD]
Welcome!
[AKANE]
I wonder what I should get.
Um, excuse me!
I want to order pork belly fried
rice, plus shrimp in chili,
six of those black sesame
dumpling things and let's see.
What else do I want?
Oh! And do you have
any tomato juice?
[FIGHTER HIKARI]
Grand Knight Beam Blade!
[ASSASSINATION FIGHTER SPECTER]
Well, well. How interesting...
[AKANE]
It's okay. You can dig in.
Alright. If you say so.
[YUTA] This isn't going to be
poisoned or anything, is it?
[AKANE] Yup. It's exactly
as you're thinking.
[gasps]
The girl that lived here.
I ordered my kaiju to erase her.
And poof, no more.
But why? What did she ever
do to you that was so bad tha--
The special dog.
Huh?
The food I gave you!
Those girls went and smushed
it with the volleyball.
I was like, "you've got
to be kidding me."
Huh?
Huh? Don't you remember?
[YUTA]
That's not...
Just for that?
That was your reason?
Yep.
You know, when someone dies,
there are other people
who suffer as well.
Their families
and their friends!
[AKANE]
Yeah, that's possible.
Oh! Good! He's here!
[ALEXIS] Hello, hello!
You may call me Alexis Kerib.
Apologies. I didn't
mean to show up late.
You must be Yuta Hibiki.
I've heard so much
about you from Akane.
[YUTA]
It's an alien.
Who is this person?
I thought you wanted to know.
"How I was able to
bring kaiju to life".
Alexis. He always
works so hard for me.
[ALEXIS grunts]
No, no.
Akane's the artist here,
and I'm simply making her
brilliant designs come to life.
[STAFF A]
Your black sesame dumplings.
[ALEXIS]
Oh, these looks delicious.
[YUTA]
What even is their goal?
[ALEXIS] Is something wrong,
Yuta Hibiki?
Please, go ahead
and help yourself.
[YUTA]
Uh, right.
[AKANE] Excuse me?
Could we get another napkin?
[ALEXIS]
Oh, thank you.
[AKANE] So why were you late?
I called a while back.
[ALEXIS] Apologies, but
something came up last minute,
so I got a late start.
[beeping]
[AKANE]
You're pulling my leg.
A-A kaiju?
[AKANE] Huh? No, I didn't
make one today.
Okay, but still...
[AKANE] If I said there isn't
a kaiju, there isn't a kaiju.
Sit down.
[ALEXIS] If it bothers you,
see for yourself.
[YUTA]
Thanks for the meal!
[YUTA grunts, gasps]
[YUTA]
What the hell is that?
[CROWD chatters]
Whoa! Are you guys seeing this?
[HASS] That is one
hundred percent a UFO.
[RIKKA]
Sorry. Restroom.
[NAMIKO, HASS]
When you gotta go...
Yuta, it's definitely
a space craft.
Yeah! The alien
invasion has started!
No way...
Alexis, what is the meaning o--?
[YUTA pants]
Hey! He's here!
Yuta! Hurry!
[YUTA] Sorry! I was out
meeting with somebody!
Gridman!
[GRIDMAN]
Let's go, Yuta!
Right!
Access... Flash!
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[MAX]
Why is it not attacking?
[BORR]
It's just gonna float there?
[RIKKA gasps]
Look out!
[GRIDMAN]
Grid Beam!
[GRIDMAN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[ALEXIS]
Welcome back home, Akane.
[AKANE] What's the deal?
Where'd that thing come from?
[ALEXIS] Oh, that. It's a kaiju
from a plan Anti devised.
You allowed Anti to
make his own kaiju?
How could you?
[ALEXIS]
It's simple.
Anti despises Gridman far
more intensely than you.
[AKANE]
Huh?
[ALEXIS]
And the stronger the hatred,
the stronger the
kaiju will be born.
[AKANE grunts]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[GRIDMAN]
Grid... Beam!
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[YUTA grunts]
There's no end to this!
They're gonna need some help!
Alright! Borr's long-distance
attacks should kick its ass!
If the Grid Beam didn't work,
what good do you think me
going out there's gonna do?
Let the flier take care of it.
Th-That's a good idea.
It's decided then.
[BORR]
Whenever you feel like it!
[VIT scoffs]
My turn? Okay, okay.
Access code. Sky Vitter.
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[VIT] Hey, sorry for
being late, Gridman!
[GRIDMAN]
Just in time, Vit!
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[GRIDMAN, VIT]
Empyrean Combine! Sky Gridman!
[VIT]
Let's fly, Gridman!
[GRIDMAN] Strange. I sense
nothing from the UFO.
[YUTA] That is weird.
But what's it mean?
[VIT]
It means this might be a trap.
Lucky Smoke Screen!
[GRIDMAN]
Grid...
Above?
[GRIDMAN shouts]
[GRIDMAN gasps]
[YUTA]
There!
[GRIDMAN]
This must be the main body!
[KAIJU sneers]
I've been waiting
for you, Gridman!
Since when can that one fly?
Damn! He's ripping
off our moves again!
[ANTI]
Eat this, Gridman!
[YUTA gasps]
Wait. What in the world?
[ANOSILLUS] I told you, outside
the city there's nothing.
A city? Up in the sky?
What's going on?
[MAX] Hm. The information
Yuta heard from that girl
may very well be
true after all.
So then... Akane really is...
How is any of this
stuff possible?
I mean, if there really
is some kind of alien...
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[KAIJU groans]
[ANTI]
You're all mine!
[VIT]
Sure about that?
[ANTI shouts]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[GRIDMAN]
Gridknight Saber... Slash!
[VIT] Not so fast!
Amp Laser Circus!
[ANTI grunts]
[ANTI yells]
[grunts]
[ALEXIS] It would appear
Anti was no good after all.
There's only one able
to make true kaiju.
And it's the one who's
truly a human, you.
Yeah... Something only I can do.
[ALEXIS]
As for that pathetic Anti.
Allow me to discipline him.
[AKANE] Please. And don't
let anyone in this room.
You met an alien life form?!
And Akane was there too?
[YUTA]
That's right.
No way, you mean that
she's with an alien?
Don't forget the city in the sky
hanging over us like a ceiling.
How's all this tie together?
So we're dealing with a god,
aliens, and a floating city.
This is, like, way too
for me much to handle.
[GRIDMAN] Then the source of
the approaching danger,
may be Akane Shinjo
and this Alexis Kerib.
[YUTA] If Kaiju are born
from Shinjo's heart,
then fighting isn't
my only mission.
For us and Gridman, there is
even more that we must do.
[ALEXIS]
Anti, a moment of your time?
You did so well out there today,
I have a reward for you.
[ANTI grunts]
[ANTI yells]
[ALEXIS chuckles]
♪