♪
[RIKKA]
Whoa. No way.
Wasn't the school destroyed
by that kaiju yesterday?
Wait, do you think
maybe Gridman
somehow fixed up
the school for us?
[HAYAKAWA]
Kaiju?
Yeah. You know,
that kaiju from last night.
The one that went on a rampage?
What?
[ONDA] Dude, Hibiki, it's a
little early for crazy talk.
But, seriously, this whole
amnesia thing is actually real?
Did you hit your head?
Come on, give the guy a break.
No one remembers the
kaiju or Gridman.
It's like their memories were
reset along with the city.
[RIKKA] How can this
even be happening?
The news hasn't said
anything about it, either.
Second of all. This feels weird.
Aren't we missing some desks?
[YUTA] Okay, you're starting to
creep me out. Who's missing?
[RIKKA]
Uh, he's right.
Tonkawa, Toiko, and a few
others' desks are gone.
[UTSUMI]
What's it mean?
Good morning, Rikka.
[HASS] Oh. Surrounded by
boys again, I see.
Would you two give
it a rest already?
Hey, by the way,
do you know why there aren't
any desks for Tonkawa,
Toiko, and the others?
Tonkawa? Toiko? Who are they?
"Who are they?" You know,
the volleyball club.
[HASS] Rikka, nobody in
our class plays volleyball.
What's with you this morning?
[YUTA]
Man, what is going on?
[UTSUMI]
Beats me.
Excuse me, teach? I think
something's wrong with Rikka.
Uh... Good to know.
[NAMIKO]
No, seriously!
She's, like, making up imaginary
friends or something.
[HASS]
Girl, just sit down.
[TEACHER] We should
do attendance, but forget it.
[NAMIKO] Oh, yeah. Rikka,
wanna hit the plaza later?
Huh? Uh, yeah, sure.
This is just way too weird.
We should ask Gridman
about it after school.
Yeah, he might know something.
Wait. Back up. The shop
is actually closed today.
'Kay. Then you can open it.
No. I happen to
have plans today.
We're kinda in the middle
of an ongoing crisis, here.
Don't you think some of
this stuff's pretty strange?
Yes, it definitely is,
but still...
Ugh...
[NAMIKO]
Well. Look at you.
Sorry. Looks like I'm opening
the shop today, after all.
Hey, it's fine, no worries!
We'll see you later.
[HASS]
Have yourself a blast!
Hey! It's not like that!
Wait a minute. You're planning
to come every day?
Yeah. It is the secret base
of the Gridman Alliance so...
Then you were serious
about that name stuff?
That's so dumb.
[UTSUMI]
It's not dumb at all!
Gridman, huh?
[school bells ringing]
Where do you plan to eat?
Sorry?
It's lunchtime.
Where are you eating?
[AKANE] Hey. Do you
really have amnesia?
[YUTA]
Hm-hm.
Whoa. That actually
sounds kinda cool.
It's not. I don't think I
could feel any less cool.
Oh, yeah! I heard you say
something funny this morning.
About a kaiju showing up?
[grunts]
[AKANE] What was that about?
C'mon, 'fess up!
[YUTA]
Uh, how can I put this?
[AKANE]
Hmm? Why so mysterious?
[YUTA] It's not like I'm trying
to hide anything. It's just...
[AKANE giggles]
[AKANE] Sorry, I'm probably
being too nosy.
[YUTA]
No, it's fine.
[AKANE]
Well, guess I'm gonna take off.
But we should do lunch
again sometime, okay?
Gridman, huh? Is that our
mysterious guest's name?
[AKANE grunts]
[gasps]
[AKANE]
I'm sorry!
Oh. Hey, come on now, sir!
Watch where you're going!
[TEACHER]
Yeah.
[RIKKA'S MOM]
The shop's closed today, so...
You all enjoy yourselves!
[RIKKA]
See you later!
[GRIDMAN]
Yo.
[YUTA]
Uh, hey.
[GRIDMAN] Yuta. You have
a mission to complete.
Um, yeah, about that.
I was hoping you could
finally explain it.
I can see his picture,
but I can't hear his voice.
[YUTA]
Wait, you still can't?
Which is totally unfair.
What's Gridman saying
to you right now?
[YUTA]
Uh, well...
[GRIDMAN]
Danger is quickly approaching.
Hello, Alexis. I'm home,
as you can see.
[ALEXIS] Well, well!
Welcome back, Akane.
Something bad
happened again, didn't it?
[AKANE] Yeah. I found
out something, though.
[ALEXIS]
Hmm? What's that?
[AKANE]
It's about our guest, actually.
He might be named Gridman.
[ALEXIS]
Oh? Gridman, huh?
[AKANE] Yeah, and it looks like
there are at least three kids
who didn't lose
their memories.
[ALEXIS]
Ah! How curious is that?
I know, right?
[YUTA] It's no use. And he said
that he was gonna explain later.
Look, we can do it
without Gridman.
We'll unravel the
mystery ourselves.
I know we can figure
out who the enemy is.
[YUTA] Enemy? This is
getting way out of hand.
You never know. It might
be aliens or somethin'.
--No way.
--Why aliens?
Well, if kaiju are appearing,
it's only natural that
aliens come next.
It's a staple of
the Ultra series.
What is that?
Oh...
Yeah, aliens.
That's right!
[door clatters]
Uh. Sorry, sir.
I'm afraid the shop's
already closed for the day.
It's the alien!
Who's that?
I have no idea.
I... I am Samurai Calibur.
He's a samurai?
Nah, he's totally an alien.
D-Danger is approaching us.
That's why we've
come here, you see.
Hold on, who's "we"?
[CALIBUR] Hm? Me and
the others, of course.
Is this where you're at?
[YUTA]
What exactly are you doing?
[RIKKA] Um, that thing
is actually for sale.
[CALIBUR]
I-I'm optimizing it.
Gridman's no good
as he is right now.
Gridman? So, you
know him, then?
[CALIBUR]
I'm done.
So fast.
[GRIDMAN] Did it work?
Can you hear me, you three?
I can hear it now!
Gridman's voice!
This is nuts.
[GRIDMAN]
You must hurry.
There is something
you all must do.
Something I must do?
[UTSUMI] Okay, you can
leave it to us, Gridman!
We'll start by investigating
the five missing people.
[YUTA]
How?
[UTSUMI] I dug up their
addresses during lunch.
Using our school's
secret weapon:
The telephone directory!
Way to creep.
[UTSUMI gasps]
[CALIBUR]
L-Let's go.
[UTSUMI]
Whoa, hold on.
Hey! Mister Samurai, wait!
That guy's gotta
be dangerous, right?
[YUTA]
Is this the right way?
I'm pretty sure
that it is, but...
I wish he'd stay on the ground.
Look at that! Kaiju!
[RIKKA]
He's right!
[YUTA]
You both see them, too?
[UTSUMI]
Yeah.
That's crazy.
Have we've been living next
to them all this time?
[CALIBUR]
W-We're here.
Rikka, if you would?
Pretty please?
Please?
Uh! Why do I have to?
[TONKAWA'S DAD]
Welcome!
Um, sir, excuse me?
Yeah?
I'm, uh, looking for a friend
of mine. Sakiru Tonkawa.
I'm Rikka Takarada
from her high school.
From her high school?
What is this? What're you doing?
[RIKKA]
Huh?
We stopped by because she
wasn't in class today.
[TONKAWA'S DAD]
Of course she wasn't.
Our girl died when she
was in middle school.
In an accident.
[RIKKA, UTSUMI]
Middle school?
But, sir, she was
there just yesterday.
Now you listen.
I think we mighta
pushed his buttons.
[RIKKA]
What does this mean?
[YUTA] She couldn't have
died during middle school.
[CALIBUR]
L-Let's go.
Hold up. Mister Samurai!
[YUTA] After that, we went to
the other four's houses.
But it was the same
story with all of them.
[AKANE]
Yes! Yes! They're dead!
[AKANE, ALEXIS laugh]
[ALEXIS]
How wonderful.
[UTSUMI]
It's scorching.
Nothing for you?
I can't do carbonated drinks.
Y'know, shaking that
won't get it out.
[RIKKA] Why is it that the
five of them are dead now?
They were fine just yesterday.
They... They were all
attacked by kaiju, so...
[RIKKA] Does this mean we're
never going to see them again?
[UTSUMI] Even though all those
people told us they were dead,
it still doesn't feel like it.
Yeah.
[RIKKA]
How can you be so calm?
I dunno. Prob'ly cuz the whole
situation hasn't sunk in yet.
Besides, Rikka, were you even
friends with Tonkawa and them?
[sighs]
[RIKKA]
What does that matter?
That's not even what
I'm talking about.
[clang]
[footsteps]
[CALIBUR]
C-Can you drink this?
Thanks, that's really
nice of you.
[RIKKA] I just don't want any
more friends to disappear.
I don't want all of our good
memories to disappear.
And for me to be the only
one left who remembers.
I can't stand the
thought of that.
I doubt anyone could, which...
which is why we have to fight.
I know. If another kaiju
appears, I want him to fight.
Because only they can do it.
Only Hibiki and Gridman
can protect my friends.
Then I think you
should tell him that.
[RIKKA]
I can't.
[AKANE]
Look! My new creation!
[ALEXIS] Wow! It's magnificent!
What will you use it for?
[giggles]
Well, I was thinking of killing
my homeroom teacher with it.
[ALEXIS]
Oh?
[AKANE] Who runs into someone
and doesn't even apologize?
So rude.
[ALEXIS]
That's not nice at all.
I know! So, I'm counting on you.
[ALEXIS] But of course.
Instance Abreaction!
[gasps]
[sirens wailing]
[YUTA]
I knew it. Another kaiju.
[CALIBUR]
One's coming?
A kaiju...
[roars]
What the hell is that?
[gasps]
[AKANE]
Oh, there you are, sir!
Hey, where are you going?
School's still in session!
You ought to be with
the students, not out here!
That was totally wild!
Watch where you're
aiming, will you?
I've gotta go.
[UTSUMI] Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa! Hold on a sec!
This is dangerous!
[YUTA] But people are
going to die again.
I've gotta go
fight with Gridman.
[UTSUMI] This is just way
out of character for you.
[YUTA]
It might be, but...
Utsumi. we're the
Gridman Alliance, right?
Well... Yeah. We are.
[YUTA]
C'mon, let's get to Junk.
[UTSUMI]
Right!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL scream]
Wow. Thank you for that!
That was too close.
Let's go, Utsumi!
Yeah!
[CALIBUR] I told you
that we'd have to fight.
So, what will you do?
Not much time.
[AKANE] I wonder if my
teacher actually died...
Well, not that it
really matters.
Gridman, please! I need
you to fight with me!
[GRIDMAN]
In this world,
I am merely energy
without substance.
Unless I merge with you,
I won't be able to fight.
Something only I can do.
Something... that I must do!
[GRIDMAN] That is your
and my Primal Acceptor.
You'll have to "Access Flash"
with me when you're ready.
Right!
Access... Flash!
[whimpers]
[YUTA] I feel so light!
Is that because of Gridman?
His color and moves
are different!
[YUTA]
I can hear you over there!
This must be the
optimized Gridman.
Yes! Go pulverize it!
[YUTA (GRIDMAN)]
Grid... Beam!
[YUTA (GRIDMAN) grunts]
It just reflected the beam!
[AKANE giggles]
My beam counter was perfect!
[ALEXIS]
Well done, Akane!
[UTSUMI]
Not this again!
[RIKKA]
He's gonna lose at this rate.
The kaiju, doesn't it
have any weak points?
No idea.
[RIKKA]
Can you stop that thing?
No, I can't.
For real?
Look, if you're a
friend of Gridman,
then please, do something
to help him out!
That, I actually can do.
Access Code: Gridman Calibur!
[CALIBUR]
Gridman! Put me to work!
[YUTA (GRIDMAN)]
Right!
Electric Great Sword!
Gridman Calibur!
What the--?!
This guy's got weapons?
[ALEXIS]
What a pesky guest.
[AKANE]
Come on, don't you lose to that!
[CALIBUR] Hey, Gridman,
let's slice it apart!
[YUTA (GRIDMAN)]
Right!
[GRIDMAN]
Grid....
[CALIBUR]
...Calibur....
[YUTA (GRIDMAN), CALIBUR]
...End!
Hell yeah!
--Hibiki.
--Yuta!
Uh. Thank you so
much for your help.
[CALIBUR]
Hm.
What was with the sword?
That wasn't even fair!
[ALEXIS] Mm-mm-mm.
Always such a violent girl.
[YUTA]
"What I must do."
I did what only I can do,
together with Gridman.
But... this destroyed city,
and the memories of the
people who live here...
...will once again be...
[RIKKA sighs]
I just got a hold of
Namiko and Hass.
They're fine.
I'm off to meet them.
Thanks for everything.
Who was that meant for?
[GRIDMAN] Yuta, thanks to you,
I was able to fight today.
Yeah, but what about all the
people we weren't able to save?
If... If you hadn't
done anything,
then more would've died.
Keep doing it. Do what
you can do... Always.
[ALL giggle]
[UTSUMI]
I knew it.
Besides us, nobody remembers
anything about the kaiju
or Gridman at all.
And the city's back
to normal again.
[UTSUMI] Damn it's hot.
Let's go inside.
[YUTA] If this stuff just keeps
repeating over and over,
then is there any real meaning
to anything I've done?
[YUTA grunts]
Hey there.
Sorry about that. My bad.
[YUTA]
No, it's okay.
[UTSUMI] Yuta, watch where
you're goin', man.
[YUTA]
Yeah, sorry.
♪