♪
[AKANE]
Good luck, okay?
I have high hopes for you.
You'll kill it, Anti.
I'll crush him, no doubt.
[RIKKA groans]
[RIKKA]
I so wanna skip today.
[YUTA]
No one remembers it, but...
...this city was
twice destroyed.
And twice, it was
put back to normal.
It's been a week
since that happened,
and there's still no sign
of my memory returning.
I'm the only one who seems
really out of place,
and it's unsettling.
--Yuta.
--[yelps]
C'mere.
Uh?
See? Look down there.
[YUTA]
Huh? Whoa, is that Calibur?
Why would he follow us here?
I dunno but he looks suspicious.
Bet he gets thrown out.
[YUTA]
No. I think he's okay.
This is just like before.
Nobody pays much
attention to Calibur.
Yeah, looks like you're right.
Hold on. Where's Rikka?
[UTSUMI]
Huh. That's a good question.
[footsteps]
[STUDENTS chattering]
Dude, if you're that
worried about her
just call her already!
[YUTA]
What're you doing?!
[phone vibrates]
[phone ringing]
No answer.
Hey, so, I think I might
be on to something.
Huh?
[UTSUMI] Well, during the
fight the other day,
I saw Calibur turn
into a giant sword.
Then, I wondered.
Is it the same way with
all the kaiju, too?
Do you think it's
possible that they could
also be humans who
have been transformed?
Huh?! If that's true, then...
...I've killed people?
Have we been fighting
human beings
the whole time
without knowing it?
Just kidding!
I can't believe that!
[YUTA]
That's... not funny at all.
All right, settle down.
[NAMIKO]
Hey, Teach. Rikka's not here.
[HASS]
Didn't call us, either.
[MALE TEACHER 2A] Well, she
never contacted the school.
Do you... need an umbrella?
[gasps]
[RIKKA]
Here. You still hungry?
[MALE TEACHER 3A] And so,
the period of adolescence
was therefore described as
a period of great transition.
We know that to be true.
In other words, "marginal
man" is a term which--
[phone ringing]
So, he has a cell phone.
[AKANE]
Hello? Anti?
Do it. Go wild.
You got it.
[screams]
[MALE TEACHER 3A] Modern day
psychological approaches
are quite different,
of course...
What the...? What now?
[crash]
Huh?!
[MALE TEACHER 3A] Particularly
notable researcher who--
Another kaiju!
[STUDENTS scream]
There's no time, c'mon!
[STUDENTS gasping]
Yuta! Hold up!
[YUTA, UTSUMI scream]
[YUTA, UTSUMI grunt, scream]
[MALE TEACHER 3A]
Okay, class, let's try...
The heck was that?
[HASS] Hot damn,
it's so freakin' close!
Too close!
[MALE TEACHER 3A]
What do we do?
[STUDENTS whimpering]
[rumbling]
A kaiju.
[YUTA, UTSUMI screaming]
[YUTA, UTSUMI groan]
[RIKKA]
Huh...?
[CALIBUR]
Y-You come, too. Let's go.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[YUTA, UTSUMI scream]
[RIKKA, YUTA, UTSUMI scream]
[AKANE] Ooh! It's so
much more impressive
seeing it up close
and in person!
Hope you'll come out to
play soon, Mister Gridman.
[shutter clicks]
[RIKKA, YUTA, UTSUMI scream]
Okay, that sucked.
Oh. Hibiki. Morning.
Rikka. I mean--
Hi, good morning.
About earlier...
[GRIDMAN] Yuta, another
kaiju has appeared. Hurry!
Right! Access flash! Let's go!
You can do it, Yuta!
[RIKKA] Guess it'll have to
wait till he comes back.
He finally showed!
[GRIDMAN grunting]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[ANTI] Gridman! I'll crush
you, you bastard!
[GRIDMAN gasps]
[YUTA]
Wait, the kaiju just talked!
So, that means it's really...
[ANTI yelling]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
Oh no, he's getting beat down.
Yuta! Pull it together!
[YUTA]
I can't fight... a human!
[RIKKA] A human?
What's he talking about?
[ANTI]
Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die!
What's going on?
Why won't Hibiki fight back?
Because...
Tell me.
Uh, it's just, it's nothing.
[GRIDMAN yells]
[RIKKA] Uh, any chance
you could transform
into a sword like you
did that other time?
Yeah, all right.
Access Code! Gridman Calibur!
[ANTI]
Get out of my sight!
[ANTI groans]
Not this again.
[GRIDMAN]
Electric Great Sword.
Gridman Calibur!
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta, if you and I fail here,
think how many could die!
[YUTA]
But!
[GRIDMAN] That includes
all of our comrades!
[ANTI yells]
[BOTH grunt]
So brilliant!
Anti can copy all his opponents'
powers! And then some!
[GRIDMAN gasps]
[YUTA]
It's fast! At this rate-- Ah!
Yuta!
[ANTI] This is the end
for you, Gridman!
[ANTI yells]
[GRIDMAN groaning]
[RIKKA gasps]
What happened?
[UTSUMI exhales]
What's going on?
Why aren't they coming back?
Where's Hibiki?
And what about Calibur?
It beat them.
No way.
He killed him.
[AKANE]
I did it. I finally won.
I did it!
[laughing]
[sighs] Ugh. Man,
I'm stiff as a board.
Uh! You scared
the hell outta me!
What're you doing?
You weren't here
all night, were you?
[RIKKA]
Yeah.
[RIKKA'S MOM] Look, sleep
in your room, wouldja?
I mean, I know the shop's
closed today, but still.
Want breakfast?
It's ready if you do.
[RIKKA]
'Kay.
What about school?
[RIKKA]
Yeah. I'll go.
[AKANE]
Aren't you excited?
A special treat for Anti's
good work. Go nuts!
[ANTI chewing]
[AKANE] Yesterday,
this boy named Utsumi
in my class was saying
he thought the true form of
kaiju might actually be humans.
Man, that couldn't be
further from the truth.
Too bad he doesn't know kaiju
don't have a true form.
Kaiju are simply kaiju.
Am I a kaiju, too, then?
Yep, you sure are.
You're a kaiju that even
eats breakfast with me!
Hey, do you think...
[UTSUMI]
Hm?
I've gotta check something!
Hey, wait up!
[UTSUMI]
This is Yuta's place.
[RIKKA]
Yeah.
[UTSUMI]
I'll push it.
[RIKKA]
Wait! Forget it. Let's go.
Huh? Then what did
we come here for?
To check for him, right?
[RIKKA]
Yeah, to check.
But what if... Hibiki...
...has actually been
dead for a long time?
Just like Tonkawa and Toiko.
I can't bring myself
to ask anyone,
'cause I mean,
what if they forgot him?
Like the others?
[RIKKA]
I'm too scared. I can't!
[footsteps]
[AKANE] Yay! Gridman is dead
and I'm on top of the world!
It's all thanks to you, Alexis!
[ALEXIS] No, no, no.
You owe it only to yourself.
You created a marvelous
auto intelligence kaiju!
That's why you won.
[AKANE, ALEXIS laugh]
[RIKKA]
Why won't Junk turn on?
How the hell am I
supposed to know that?
I've always sucked
with computers.
[RIKKA] If Calibur were here,
I bet he could fix it.
Well he's not,
so just deal with it.
[RIKKA]
I was just saying, so chill.
And don't tell me
to "deal with it."
Yeah, right. Gimme a break.
Yesterday, when
Gridman was losing,
you evaded my
question about why.
I think it's time
you explained--
No, I wasn't evading anything.
Besides, if I explained,
you wouldn't get it, anyway.
See? I knew that's
what you were doing.
I'm not an idiot.
When the hell did I say
anything like that?!
Uh! This is such
bullshit. Forget it.
The Gridman Alliance...
is disbanded.
[RIKKA]
You can't...
You can't disband it now.
[RIKKA] If you do that,
Hibiki won't have any place
to come back to.
I thought he'd be
coming back like normal.
And once he did,
I was gonna apologize for not
answering his call before.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This shop's everything
you'd expect it to be.
You're kidding!
There's a whole café
in the back?
There is, but the shop
isn't open today, so...
[MAX]
That poses a problem.
[MAX] If the shop's closed
to us, then I'm afraid
we won't be able
to support Gridman.
Huh?
You know Gridman?
[BORR] Let's see,
what'm I feelin' today.
Uh! Figures, of course it's
all stuff I don't like.
[MAX]
I think I'll have a latte.
Excuse me?!
Two lattes, please.
Oh, sorry, one for me, too.
[BORR]
Make that three lattes!
[VIT] Um, can one of those
be a toast combo?
[BORR]
There's a combo?
Make that two combos!
Oh, they're only
served after two p.m.
[VIT]
No way.
Where the heck is Calibur?
Aren't we s'posed to meet here?
Uh. I'm sorry,
but I think... he died
together with Gridman.
Hey, brat, where did you come
from and who invited you here?
Fret not, Calibur isn't dead,
and neither is Gridman.
[BOTH gasp]
So, that means Hibiki
must be alive, too!
Who in the world is that?
Beats me.
Well, he's... He's my friend!
Well, if that's the case,
then, why haven't you
asked him yourself?
Ask him myself? How would I?
Tell me this: do you
normally ask strangers
how your friends are doing?
Don't you have a number
of ways to contact him?
[UTSUMI]
I don't get what you're saying.
Oh. There are.
I'm gonna call him!
C'mon, stop that,
you know that can't
be what he means!
--[YUTA] Hello?
--[gasps] He picked up!
--[UTSUMI] Seriously?
--[YUTA] Who, who's this? Rikka?
[RIKKA] Mm-hm. Listen, where
are you right now, Hibiki?
[YUTA]
Where? Um. I don't really know.
Yuta! Are you okay?!
[YUTA]
Utsumi?
Yeah, it's me, bud!
It's so good to hear you-- Ow!
Damn, that hurt!
Hand that here.
Talk to me, Calibur. Hey.
[CALIBUR]
B-Borr?
There you are.
Get back here, right now!
[CALIBUR]
No, not yet.
Why not?
[CALIBUR] G-Gridman's
restored and on standby.
If that kaiju appears again,
we'll ambush and defeat it.
B-But we've been waiting,
and it hasn't shown.
[BORR] Huh, that's weird.
Well, whatever.
Just get back here already, now.
[UTSUMI, RIKKA]
Calibur!
[MAX]
Gridman.
We're all gathered now.
You can still fight, can't you?
[GRIDMAN]
Of course.
--[RIKKA] Hibiki!
--[UTSUMI] Yuta!
[ALEXIS] Akane, you're
not going to like this.
[AKANE]
Hm?
[ALEXIS] It seems our guest
was alive all along.
No way! Gridman's still alive?!
[ALEXIS] You know,
why not just enjoy it?
Isn't that what the
kaiju's for, after all?
That's true. Anti!
[ANTI]
I'll be there.
[ANTI yells]
[ANTI]
Gridman. You're an eyesore!
I'll make you disappear!
[ANTI]
Die! Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die! Die!
Crap, this one's so fast.
[MAX]
Perhaps I'll go.
Access Code:
Battle. Tracto. Max!
[MAX]
Tanker Cannon!
[ANTI grunting]
[MAX] I'm here, Gridman!
Let's combine!
[GRIDMAN]
Affirmative!
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[GRIDMAN, MAX]
Heracles Combine!
Max Gridman!
What is that? It doesn't
make any sense.
[ANTI]
What are you trying to pull?
[ANTI, GRIDMAN grunt]
[GRIDMAN]
Are you a human?
[ANTI]
A human? Hell no!
I'm a kaiju!
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[ANTI yells]
[GRIDMAN yells]
[ANTI]
I was born just to crush you!
Obliterating you is my
one and only duty!
[GRIDMAN]
Then I need not be concerned.
I will defeat you!
[ANTI]
This is the part where you die!
[MAX]
Max...
[GRIDMAN]
Grid...
[GRIDMAN, MAX]
...Beam!
It's the same attack as Anti's!
[GRIDMAN, MAX yelling]
[GRIDMAN yells]
[ANTI yells]
[beeping]
[ANTI]
I ran out of time?
Shit!
Grid... man.
[ANTI]
I hate you.
[beeping]
[BOTH gasp]
[UTSUMI]
Yuta!
Hey, man!
[RIKKA] If you were alive
you should've said so.
Well, I didn't think a
phone would actually--
Listen! About not answering
your call before...
Sorry!
[YUTA]
Huh?
That one is gonna be a handful.
Uh-huh.
The thing to know is,
phones are linked to lives.
[YUTA]
Just a sec. Who're they?
Who're these people?
[UTSUMI]
Uh...
[GRIDMAN] They're the Neon
Genesis Junior High Students.
Allies of mine and yours.
--Allies?
--[UTSUMI] Junior high?
[MAX]
Yuta Hibiki.
From now on,
let's fight together.
Right!
[footsteps]
Whoa! Wow, what a crowd.
So are these guys new customers?
♪