♪
[AKANE] Why the hell does
he keep standing in my way?
Plus, he gets
stronger every time.
[ALEXIS]
Even I remain in the dark
as to the true
form of our guest.
But you have your suspicions,
don't you?
Yeah. Yuta Hibiki.
I've got a feeling
he's Gridman, but still,
there's no way to
know for sure.
[ALEXIS] We'll have to
confirm it somehow.
And do so with extreme care.
Nope. Can't do it. I'll melt.
It's a bus day.
[footsteps]
[AKANE]
Morning!
[RIKKA]
Mm? Oh! Good morning.
[RIKKA] So do you
always take the bus?
[AKANE] On days
like this, definitely.
Or I'd burn to a crisp.
[RIKKA]
Yeah. Same.
[BOTH giggle]
[RIKKA] Feels like
it's been forever, huh?
[AKANE]
What does?
[RIKKA] Well, you know,
our houses are pretty close.
We used to walk together
in the mornings.
But lately, I guess we haven't
talked to each other much.
[AKANE] You really think so?
Huh, I never noticed.
[RIKKA]
Huh?
[ANNOUNCEMENTS, BUS DRIVER]
Departing.
Lately, it seems like you've
been talking with Hibiki
quite a lot. How come?
Huh? I don't know if
I'd say that. It's normal.
Did you not hear me?
The question was,
why are you talking?
[FEMALE BUS ANNOUNCEMENTS] Next
stop, Tsutsujidai High School.
Next stop,
Tsutsujidai High School.
In front of Bashar, the used
books and media store.
[AKANE]
Got you!
[RIKKA chuckles]
What the heck!
[HASS]
Rikka!
[RIKKA]
Hm?
[HASS] You don't have
anything Saturday, right?
[NAMIKO]
Please say you're free!
[RIKKA]
Just tell me what's going on.
[HASS] Arcadia promised
to hang out with us!
[NAMIKO] Well? Isn't that nuts?
I'm so stoked!
[RIKKA]
Back up. Who's Arcadia?
[NAMIKO]
You mean you don't know?
[HASS]
Didn't you watch the video?
[RIKKA]
What video?
[ARCADIA MEMBERS]
This is Heisei's last utopia.
And we're Arcadia!
[ALL]
What's up?
And Arcadia's topic
of the day is:
Heard of cheese fondue?
[TAKATO]
Yeah. Sure.
[YAMATO] Well today we're
gonna be testing the limits
of cheese fondue.
Aren't they amazing?
[HASS] Not only will Takato
be there, but also Yamato!
It's a miracle!
Yeah. Which is which?
[NAMIKO] You are gonna
come with us, aren't you?
[HASS] We already said
there'd be four of us.
I'll check my schedule.
[AKANE] Oh? If you need
a fourth, maybe I could go.
[NAMIKO, HASS]
Would you?!
If Akane's there, our squad
will be unbeatable!
[NAMIKO] Unbeatable?
So who are we fighting?
You're going with us, right?
[NAMIKO]
You're crazy.
[HASS giggles]
For sure.
[RIKKA humming]
Okay, here's your order.
Sorry about the wait.
Why is she in such a good mood?
[UTSUMI]
No idea.
Hey, Rikka. Why're you
in such a good mood?
[RIKKA] There's not any
reason in particular.
But I was invited to go
out with some people
this upcoming Saturday.
Some guys. I think
they're in college
and have their own video
series or something.
[BOTH gasp]
[RIKKA] Namiko, Hass and,
Akane are also going.
[YUTA, UTSUMI] They're all
totally going on a group date!
[RIKKA] It's been ages since
I hung out with Akane.
[RIKKA gasps]
For you.
Thanks. I could have
gotten it, though.
[VIT] Sure, but it seemed
a little dangerous.
Really? I didn't think so.
[YUTA] Wait a minute.
Does Rikka like older guys?
[GRIDMAN] What's wrong, Yuta?
You seem troubled.
What? Me? No! I don't know
what you're talking about!
[UTSUMI grunts] This can't
be true. It's impossible.
Akane Shinjo on a group date?
[YUTA] Huh? I thought you told
me you didn't even like Shinjo.
Never said that. I only
said she was unapproachable.
[UTSUMI grunts] Why would
such a beautiful and miraculous
creature go out with a pack
of worthless college creeps!
You guys are acting so pathetic.
If you're that interested,
then tag along.
Or you'll be too late.
[BOTH]
Too late?
[GRIDMAN] Yuta. No matter
how fierce the enemy is,
we must face them and fight.
[UTSUMI] Even Gridman
thinks we should do this.
It's settled. Let's go!
[UTSUMI]
Oh, we will...
[RIKKA] What are those two
getting so worked up about?
I can assure you, it's dumb.
I'm Takato.
Imai.
Arii here.
And Yamato.
[HASS] My name's Hass,
but you know that.
I'm Namiko.
[GROUP chatters]
[RIKKA] I'm not sure
if I can handle this.
[AKANE]
Me either.
You two joining us?
Well?
Guess so...
[UTSUMI] Akane Shinjo's smiling
at them. That's so not fair!
Keep your cool, Utsumi!
[BORR chuckels]
Let's move!
[UTSUMI]
Yeah!
[HASS] Do you guys get, like,
tons of paid promotions?
[IMAI]
Yeah, kinda.
But we never talk about
things we don't like.
[HASS]
That's so interesting.
I'm not following any of this.
Hey. So you get along pretty
well with Hibiki, right?
Oh. I don't know. I mean we
talk more than before, I guess.
[AKANE]
There's something I want to ask.
Question. You two go
to the same school?
Yeah?
So, why're you wearing
different uniforms?
Well, our school's pretty
lax on the dress code.
Oh yeah?
Akane, are you...?
I know! We should all
create a group!
[ARII]
Now there's an idea!
[HASS]
Okay, I'll handle it!
[AKANE giggles]
So. I was asking
about Hibiki and...
[YAMATO] Whoa! Kudos on
your icon selection, Akane!
Alien Baltan, right?
That? I kinda picked
it completely at random.
Aww...
[ARII] Alien Baltan.
Sure brings back memories.
[AKANE] What the hell's wrong
with these old dudes?
[AKANE] Oh my gosh,
I'm so sorry.
I've gotta get
home before curfew!
[NAMIKO]
Wha-- So early?
[AKANE] I'm really sorry!
I'd stay if I could!
Bye. See you later.
[ALL]
Aw...
[AKANE]
This sucks.
Now to find which
room Rikka's in.
In the shortest amount of time!
Did you go to stalker school
or is this a natural talent?
[UTSUMI]
Huh?
[MAN A]
♪ Don't pull away! ♪
[YUTA] Whoa, whoa, Calibur!
You can't just barge into rooms!
But, but I thought we were
looking for somebody.
Yeah! Discretely!
Someone's coming! Hide quick!
[TAKATO] I wonder why
she really had to take off.
[HASS]
Ah. Akane is such a princess.
[YAMATO] Guess we'll just have
to check out the next place
without her.
[inaudible]
[gasps]
We've gotta see where
they're headed!
Nah, we're done here.
What?
Akane Shinjo's already
left to go home.
[YUTA]
Huh?
[BORR]
Okay, we'd better scatter.
Stalking is a serious
crime after all.
[VIT]
See you later.
But, come on, you guys. Argh...
Clear off!
[AKANE huffs]
Whatever.
[AKANE]
You want to help? Fine.
There are four people I
want you to kill for me.
I refuse. I was created
solely to defeat Gridman.
Unless he's my target, I won't--
[YUTA] I completely
lost track of them.
What if I am too late,
and Rikka's already...?
[YUTA grunts]
[MAX]
What are you doing?
[YUTA]
Huh?
Have you perhaps lost your way?
[ALEXIS] Welcome back, Akane.
Have you made progress on..?
[ALEXIS]
Hm?
[AKANE sighs]
[AKANE] Doing it like I have
been won't cut it anymore.
[YUTA]
It's gone.
I lost my memory and I don't
know how to get it back.
[RIKKA] If you are just
pretending to have amnesia,
then you really suck.
I think I said something
important to Rikka.
The only problem is I
have no idea what it was.
So right now--
Do you have feelings
for this young lady?
[YUTA gasps]
What? That's not what I was--
Don't you like her?
[YUTA]
Uh...
Don't you like her?
Yeah. Probably.
[MAX] Probably, huh? It's truly
vexing watching you two.
But... it's not bad.
[phone rings]
Yo, what's going on?
[IMAI] It's awful!
Arii was... He was...!
Hey, slow down. What happened?
[IMAI yells]
[TAKATO sighs]
Well that was odd.
[TAKATO]
Uh?
[TAKATO] Wait! What the..?
Not me! No, no, no, no, no!
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Happy Sunday!
You and your friends seem to
be getting along nicely today.
Did any of them ask
you to hang out
or did you just sit
down uninvited?
Wow. Full-swing puberty.
No one minds, right?
Look some customers.
Oh, it's just Yuta.
Yep, just me.
Going somewhere?
[RIKKA]
Mm-hm. What's up?
Oh, um, it's nothing.
[RIKKA grunts]
[UTSUMI] Yuta! Come on over
here and grab a seat.
Coming!
I'm heading out!
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Where're you off to?
I promised my friends
I'd tag along.
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Moody.
Unbelievable. She doesn't care
about the Gridman Alliance.
Lame.
She promised them.
[HASS sighs] Sucks we had to
split up so early last night.
If only Akane didn't have to
bail on us out of nowhere.
Yeah. I wanted a chance
to talk with her too.
Personally, I was
hoping for a chance
to talk more with Yamato.
[HASS]
Me too.
[YAMATO]
This is Heisei's last utopia.
Arcadia here and I want to dive
right into the video today.
It's been a while...
That's weird. Where are
the other three?
[NAMIKO]
Huh? What do you mean?
Arcadia's supposed to
have four people in it.
[HASS]
It's always been just the one.
[RIKKA]
It's a kaiju.
The three disappeared and
now the world's reset.
But why would it target
them specifically?
[RIKKA] At least I know
Namiko and Hass are safe.
[AKANE]
Thanks for coming yesterday.
Oh, hey. Are you doing okay?
Thank goodness.
That just leaves...
[chair clatters]
[NAMIKO]
Hm?
Sorry, I just remembered there's
an errand I need to run.
I'll see you later!
[HASS] Sorry, I just
remembered there's an errand
I need to run.
Like she thinks she's
in some old drama.
[UTSUMI]
Planning on going out today?
[RIKKA'S MOM] Well, I've gotta
do some shopping eventually.
[UTSUMI]
In that case...
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta. Are you troubled?
Yeah. I have been ever
since yesterday.
[GRIDMAN] Is it something
I can help you with?
I am your ally, after all.
Thanks a lot, but I need
to handle this on my own.
How long do I have to wait
until I get my memory back?
[GRIDMAN]
I feel the same.
For some reason, I cannot
remember the past either.
However, what I do
know is my mission.
To save this city from
approaching danger.
[YAMATO]
Hm? Hey! There you are.
I wasn't expecting
to hear from ya.
You're safe!
[YAMATO]
What?
[RIKKA] Uh. I don't exactly
know how to put this, but.
I think your friends were
targeted and made to disappear,
and since they
vanished that means
you're probably
going to be next.
[YAMATO]
Sorry, you totally lost me.
[RIKKA]
I figured I would.
[YAMATO] If you wanna talk,
I'm down for that.
Let's go find someplace nearby.
Whoa, I think you're
getting the wrong idea.
--[KAIJU A roars]
--[RIKKA gasps]
Huh. You hear that sound?
I knew it would
come after you.
Wait. It?
[RIKKA]
Come on, we've gotta run!
[YAMATO]
Hold up, Rikka!
Your life's in danger!
Yeah, right.
Danger from what exactly?
Uh, whatever's going on,
I shoulda brought my camera
to make an episode!
Yeah! That's number four!
You should get out of there
while you still can, Rikka!
[RIKKA]
What the... It won't come off!
The hell is going on here?
[RIKKA gasps]
[KAIJU A roars]
[gasps]
[CALIBUR grunts]
[RIKKA gasps]
L-Let's go.
It's that guy again!
[ALEXIS] More than likely,
he's one of Gridman's comrades.
Hello?
[MAX] Got it.
Another kaiju has appeared.
It attacked the
college boy and Rikka.
[YUTA gasps]
[MAX]
But they're fine at the moment.
Thank goodness.
[GRIDMAN]
A kaiju even I couldn't sense?
You don't think they're somehow
adapting to deal with us?
If that's the case,
there must be--
[BORR]
[UTSUMI grunts]
Son of a...
Shut up and save it for later.
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta!
Understood.
Let's do this, Gridman!
Access... Flash!
[grunts]
[KAIJU A roars]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
No! You mean they
already found it?
[roars]
[gasps]
It's Gridman!
[grunting]
[yells]
Looks like it's gonna be
a two-on-one battle!
Aw, man. That's such a pain.
Calibur. I know
you just returned,
but Gridman is
need of assistance.
--[CALIBUR] All right.
--[RIKKA] For real?
I say we all lend him a hand.
Do I have to?
[ALL]
Access code...!
[KAIJU A, GRIDMAN grunting]
[ANTI] Outta my way!
I'm gonna crush him!
[ANTI grunts]
What the...?
What are you doing, Anti?!
Must've had a change of heart.
Since the kaiju's distracted,
now's our chance!
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[GRIDMAN stutters]
[ALL stutter]
How come they stopped?
They froze like a computer.
It must have been too
much for Junk to handle.
[UTSUMI] Shit! It's over!
What do we do?
You think restarting
it might work?
What?! You can't just
unplug the power!
[RIKKA]
Why not?
[UTSUMI]
What did you do?
Stop blaming me.
[UTSUMI]
Why isn't it booting up?!
Don't kick it!
It's not a damn CRT!
[YUTA groans] Oh hey,
what the heck happened?
A certain someone cut
the power supply to Junk!
But it's on now, so I fixed it.
[YUTA sighs]
That seemed to have caused
some kind of interference.
[UTSUMI] It appears we can't
sortie all four of you at once.
Then who's the strongest
one out of the group?
[YUTA]
Hm?
[ANTI] Show yourself!
Where'd you go, Gridman?
[GRIDMAN]
Right here!
[ANTI]
Where?!
[MAX]
Let's do it, Gridman!
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[GRIDMAN, MAX]
Heracles Combine!
Max Gridman!
[YUTA]
We're running low on energy!
[MAX]
No problem!
[GRIDMAN, MAX]
Super Lightning Kick!
[ANTI]
Prepare to die, Gridman!
[grunts]
[YUTA]
Whoa.
[UTSUMI] Man, you cut it
pretty close this time.
I know.
Welcome back.
[YUTA]
Uh?
Nice work out there.
[YUTA] Uh... Yeah.
Thanks, Rikka.
[RIKKA]
Hm?
Though, I think you're the
only reason we won today.
[RIKKA]
Don't you know it!
--[YUTA, RIKKA laugh]
--[GRIDMAN] Mm-hm.
[UTSUMI] Wish I could've
seen you all appear
at the same time, though.
[BORR] You sure have
a lot of opinions...
[YUTA] So, hey.
That thing Saturday.
How'd it go?
[RIKKA] Huh? Oh. I shouldn't
have gone in the first place.
The boys took off not long after
so I ended up listening to
Namiko and Hass complain
at the restaurant.
Huh...
[YUTA] No. I can't let
this moment get away!
Come on, me! Go for it!
So, um, do you wanna
grab food, if you're free?
It's like you read my mind!
I am practically starving!
[YUTA]
Seriously?
[RIKKA] But I'm not sure I can
find a place that'll seat all
of us. I think we're
limited to skewers.
Or maybe a buffet.
[YUTA]
Yeah. Go figure.
[MThose two are truly
vexing to watch.
[phone rings]
[AKANE sighs]
[YAMATO]
Hey. It's Yamato.
So anyway, I'm planning my next
video and... Hello? Akane?
You there?
[AKANE] I literally have zero
motivation to go to school!
[ALEXIS] You worked
exceptionally hard
this time. Which means...
[AKANE] Don't worry. It is true
I have been on edge lately.
But now whenever I imagine
how I'll crush Gridman, well,
I get so excited. I swear
I can barely contain myself!
[ALEXIS]
As long as you're having fun,
I'm enjoying the experience too.
[ALEXIS chuckles]
[RIKKA grunts] It is
definitely another bus day.
Where is she?
[bus honks]
[RIKKA]
I wonder why kaiju only show up
in the same places I go?
[RIKKA] Is it because of me?
♪