[JENDA ]
How many intruders and where?
[LUBBOCK]
Judging by the reaction of my
barrier I'd say about eight.
They're getting a little
close to the hideout
if you ask me!
If they were clever enough
to sniff us out,
we should assume
they're tribal assassins.
Move quickly!
Don't let them leave here alive.
You're still a little new
to go up against a
big group like this.
So try to be careful!
The first thing
is to let your body get a good
feel for the battlefield!
Right!
And the second thing is...
Please call me either
"Handsome" or "Bro".
You got it, Bro!
Yeah! Now we're talkin!
Hey, check this out.
(deep breath)
Incursio!
Whoa!
(swhooshing sounds)
[BULAT] Yah!
(laughs) So cool!
[BULAT] This is the
Imperial Arms Incursio.
[TATSUMI] I don't know
what Imperial Arms are,
but, man, that was awesome!
[BULAT] Ah, good, I see
you recognize its greatness!
It's them.
[BULAT]
Now's your chance to see what
Imperial Arms are all about.
Yeah!
[ASSASSIN] That's the girl
from the wanted poster.
That means Night Raid must
be around here somewhere.
She's a pretty little thing,
huh?
Let's not bang her up too bad.
I wanna have some fun
with her first.
Huh?
Wha?
Be careful.
You've entered enemy
territory, y'know.
Oh, shit!
(gaahh...)
You bitch!
I'm gonna make you pay for that!
(choking)
What's going on?
It's poison?!
It only takes one strike.
[ASSASSIN]
Crap, they spotted us.
But now I know Night Raid's
hideout is somewhere near here.
That kind of intel
is worth a fortune.
I've got to get
back to the base.
[MINE]
Well, he's made it pretty far.
Bummer, I really don't
like revealing my location.
(smirk)
[ASSASSIN] You're mine!
(ack!)
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Sheele.
Nice timing! That was just
enough danger to power up!
(increasing power whine)
(gunshot)
Huh?
(screams in pain)
Sweet! Bullseye!
The bigger the trouble I'm in,
the more powerful my
beautiful Pumpkin becomes!
[LEONE] Hmm?
That sounded like
Pumpkin just now.
I'm surprised she puts up
with that finicky thing.
When I go into beast mode
I can just beat the living
daylights outta my enemies!
Much more fun!
[LUBBOCK]
Oooh, it was a lady tugging my
strings this whole time.
(stretching sound)
Please just spare my life!
I'll do anything you want!
Noooo way.
[ASSASSIN] (painful whimpering)
I've seen way too many guys wind
up dead after a girl says that.
(snick)
(thump)
Maaan, what a waste.
Why does this job have to be so
disappointing sometimes?
Yaaahh!
(heavy breathing)
Look out!
[ASSASSINS] Hyah!
[BALUT] Yah!
He's... so strong!
So this...
(patter of falling blood)
this is the power...
of Night Raid.
[BULAT]
You still alive, Tatsumi?
Huh?
Uh, yeah!
Then everything's fine!
I can already tell
you've got some talent!
Yep!
(owl hooting)
Night Raid...
They're killers...
But they're bringing about
a revolution.
Man, I really have found a
crazy group of friends, huh?
Heh!
(waaah! panting)
(shivers)
Why'd I dream of him
of all people?!
[SAYO] The Imperial Capital!
There's a giant wall
surrounding the whole city,
and the canals are
full of trading ships!
There's so much to see!
[IEYASU] (snickers)
And don't forget all those sexy,
sophisticated city women!
[SAYO] (grrr...)
Oooh!
Gross!
[IEYASU] (ungghh)
Hey, what was that for?!
(laughing)
Sayo... Ieyasu...
I'll do my best for you guys.
I promise.
Hmm?
Is something the matter?
Huh? Oh hey, Sheele.
I'm fine...
I'm supposed to be training
with Mine today,
but she hasn't come out
of her room yet.
Spoiled little brat.
[SHEELE] Yeah, well...
Mine does have a habit
of sleeping in.
Seriously?! This is her job!
I'm so sorry for
the inconvenience.
I'll go wake her up now.
[JENDA] Wait. Let Tatsumi do it.
[SHEELE] Huh?
[TATSUMI] What? Why me?
Because you're her
subordinate for today.
Waking up your supervisor is
part of an assassin's job.
(grrr... tch!) Okay, fine.
I wasn't aware that
we had that rule.
(chuckles)
Consider it another test.
Huh?
[TATSUMI] Hey, Mine!
You just gonna sleep
all day or... (urk)
[MINE] (shrieks)
(explosion)
Hmm?
(aaahhhh...)
You coulda killed me!
Well, I missed!
You filthy pervert!
How dare you dodge when you know
you deserve to die?!
Oh, whatever!
If you hadn't slept in so late,
then I wouldn't have been
ordered to come get youuu...
(powering up whine)
Maybe so, but haven't YOU
ever heard of a thing called
KNOCKING?!
(repeated explosions)
Hey, is there some kind of
festival going on?!
She's really going all out.
Tatsumi's in for a long day.
I used to think
the capital was great,
but now I can see how
miserable the people are.
Hey! Pervert, hurry up!
What's the hold‐up, country boy?
[TATSUMI] Uh!
Let's move it! Chop chop!
[TATSUMI] (grrr...)
Aren't you supposed to be my
faithful servant for the day?
Servant?!
That's what the boss said.
No, I'm just training under you.
There IS a difference, you know!
Yeah, and the operative word
there is "under".
C'mon, we don't have
a lot of time!
Wha‐ Hey, wait!
Hmph!
[TATSUMI] Hey, Mine?
[MINE] What?
[TATSUMI] Don't these people
look unhappy to you?
[MINE] They live in fear
of the government
AND the economy sucks.
Most everyone's either at rock
bottom or on their way down.
You wouldn't be
that chipper either.
(men laughing & a child crying)
[PUNK] Go ahead and cry.
Nobody's listenin'!
(continued laughing & crying)
[TATSUMI] Hey, what do
you two think your do‐
[MINE] Shouldn't you two jerks
be picking on someone
your own size?
You gonna do something about it?
It's fine. This little
girl's a refugee from
outside the country.
I mean, she could turn out
to be a traitor any second.
So could I.
[PUNKS] Huh?
Tatsumi?
Got it.
(snick, snick)
(yaahhh!) (gasp)
(waahhh!)
Hmph.
[GIRL] Thank you for saving me.
[MINE] Don't thank me.
[GIRL] (gasp)
[MINE] Just grow up strong so
you can protect yourself, okay?
Ah...
I hate to ask,
but is it safe for you
to wander around in broad
daylight like this?
Y'know?
[MINE] Huh? Why not?
They've only identified
four of us so far.
Guess that makes sense.
Huh?
Wait, who's that guy
in the middle?
[MINE] That's Bulat.
Ohhh, Bulat.
(gah!) Tha... that's BRO?!
That picture's from back
in his army days.
He changed his look whenever
he signed with Night Raid.
[TATSUMI]
That looks nothing like him!
[BULAT] Ah, hah.
Oh man, that's all I need
is another image
to haunt me in my dreams.
Anyway the Boss gave this
mission to you and me
BECAUSE we can
walk around freely.
Understand?
[TATSUMI] Oh, okay!
I was wondering why we were
patrolling this part of town.
Good! Now it's time for our
retail investigation!
[TATSUMI] I don't know what
that means, but WOOHOO!
[MINE] Ahhhh... What a day!
Nothing makes me happier
than a brand new pink dress!
Yeah, whatever...
Isn't it wonderful to have
a whole day to goof off?
Yeah, whatever...
Well, the mission's complete!
What the hell?!
We did nothing but shop all day!
Welp, Get over it!
[TATSUMI](owwww!)
[MINE]
Have you already forgotten
that I'm above you?
Good servants don't
question their masters.
[TATSUMI] (ouch!)
You should be grateful
that I deemed you
[TATSUMI] (ah! uh!)
worthy enough to carry my bags!
[TATSUMI] (ow! ah! ow!)
Yeah well you're not gonna be
my boss forever, you know!
Plus, nothing we did
counts as training!
What? You think you can
just waltz in here
and be on my level?
You do seem pretty confident in
your skills as a swordsman...
but you haven't seen nearly
as much combat as me.
[TATSUMI] I get it.
Huh?
I'm new...
So there are going to be some
things about this job
that I don't get yet.
But still!
I am gonna keep on fighting!
For Sayo and Ieyasu!
Ah... (sighs)
Akame and Bulat have
high hopes for you,
but I have my doubts.
(crowd murmuring)
So what's that all about?
[MINE] It's an execution.
They're pretty common here.
(crowd murmuring)
(gasps)
(prisoners groaning)
How can they do this to people?
[MINE] It's the minister who
supports this sort of cruelty.
[PRISONER] (groaning)
Ultimately, he put the child
emperor on the throne so he
could be in control.
As for me...
[PRISONER] (cries out in pain)
I'll never end up like this.
I am going to survive this hell
no matter what happens!
The Minister, huh?
What kind of monster
is this guy?
Administrator Shoi...
For speaking out publicly
against Our policies
and interfering with
matters of state,
We decree you shall be
drawn‐and‐quartered!
(gasps)
(shocked reactions)
Did We make the right decision,
Minister?
(footsteps approaching)
(chortles)
Oh yes, Your Highness.
You're the wisest ruler the
Empire could ever dream of.
Is that meat AGAIN?
You eat that a lot.
[MINISTER] (laughs)
I want to enjoy it now,
while I'm young and healthy.
Buono, buono!
(discontented grumblings)
[SHOI] Your Majesty, the
minister is deceiving you!
Please! I implore you!
Open your ears and hear
the voice of the people!
Well, Minister, did you hear
what he just said?
Seems the poor fellow's
lost his mind.
Right! You've never
lead me astray before,
so this man MUST be insane!
(quaking in fear)
My old friend...
[SHOI] (argghhh!)
Why must it end this way?
No, please! Your Grace if you
don't stop him,
he'll lead the empire into ruin!
Please... Your Grace.
No need to worry.
You can count on me
to look after
that beautiful wife
you're leaving behind.
I'll be sure to satisfy
all her needs.
And I do mean ALL of them.
(evil chuckle)
(struggles)
Nooo! You can't let this happen!
He can't do this!
He must be stopped!
Someone... anyone...
I'm begging you...
That man is a demon!
Can't any of you see that?!
Please! Pleeeaaase!!!!
[JENDA]
Night Raid has a new mission.
This time our target
is a distant relative
of Minister Honest: Iokal.
He's been using the
minister's name so that
he can kidnap innocent women
and then beat them to death.
Iokal also has
five mercenary guards.
They're equally guilty.
I'm counting on you guys.
Now, go take him out!
[TATSUMI]
So that's Iokal's mansion.
It's enormous.
Hey, Mine.
[MINE] What?
Is that one of those
Imperial Arms things too?
Yep! Its name is Pumpkin.
It gets more deadly the more
danger I find myself in.
BUT a girl like me is hardly
ever in any real danger.
How on earth did you figure out
how to make something like that?
Nobody makes Imperial Arms,
stupid.
Jeez, they're ancient,
legendary weapons.
I'm amazed by the things
you don't know.
[TATSUMI] (grrr...)
I don't need a risk factor
this far away.
I'll shoot him as soon as
he sets foot outside.
Right, and as soon as you
splatter him,
it's my job to make sure you
don't get hurt on the way back!
Leave it to me!
Heh!
I'll keep my expectations low.
(long, slow breath)
(ah!)
She's so determined...
I can almost feel
how focused she is!
[MINE] Here he comes.
(uh‐uh) Where?
[TATSUMI] Ah! Okay, I see him,
but those other guys
aren't on the hit list!
That's fine.
How is that fine?
You'll never make
the shot from here.
They are irrelevant.
Irrelevant?
No, don't!
We can't shoot innocent pe‐
(gunshot)
(uh!)
(urk)
(aaahh... aaahhh...)
[MINE]
Oh, I should let you know,
I'm kind of a badass,
sniper genius.
[MERCENARY]
We must find Lord Iokal's
killer at all costs!
[MERCENARY 2] If we don't, the
minister will have our heads!
[MERCENARY 3]
Right! He can't be too far!
[MERCENARIES] (huh?)
[LEONE] What do we have here?
Nice of you guys to save us
the trouble of chasin' you down.
Ah, man!
The escape route is not ideal.
Think they've finished off
the guards yet?
Those guards trained at the
Imperial Fist Temple.
[MONKS] (yah! yah! yah!)
It may take a little while.
[TATSUMI]
That's the best martial arts
temple in the Empire.
Guess you get what's coming
to you if you mess with
the minister's family.
Yeah. He was using his family's
influence to get ahead.
[TATSUMI] (ugh!)
[MINE]
I hate that more than anything!
(climbing)
Sounds like there's
a story there.
[MINE] (hmph) I feel like being
nice to you right now,
so I'll tell you the
story behind that.
[TATSUMI]
Didn't even have to ask!
I was born into one of the
tribes on the western border.
That means half of
my blood is foreign.
The villagers treated me
terribly because of it,
and no one showed me
an ounce of respect.
My childhood
was a nightmare.
But the Revolutionary Army
formed an alliance with
the western tribe.
So if we do end up
having a new nation,
people will stop caring
about our differences!
And no more kids will have to go
through what I did growing up.
I will not allow anybody else to
ever suffer such intolerance!
Wow, Mine...
Not to mention after everything
I've accomplished in the
name of revolution,
I'll get loads of reward
money and grow old in
the lap of luxury!
(rich girl laugh)
[TATSUMI] (grrr...)
(meowrrr!)
Oh man, that felt so incredible!
That was a rather pleasant
challenge, wasn't it?
[AKAME] Something's not right.
I thought the Boss said we were
supposed to kill five.
Aw man, I didn't
get to kill anybody!
So I guess there's one left.
Too bad, Lubb.
I'm dockin' your pay.
WHA?! You can't do that!
[LEONE] (hee hee) Wanna bet?
(gasps)
[AKAME] Tatsumi...
[MINE]
This is the rendezvous point.
Guess we're all done.
Not until we report back in,
remember?
[MINE] Ha! You sound like Akame.
(ah!) Look out!
[MINE] (ah!)
[TATSUMI] (ugh)
Tatsumi! (unh)
Who are you?
[INSTRUCTOR] I must say
I've outdone myself.
[MINE] You're a fighter
from the temple.
[INSTRUCTOR] I am. Assistant
instructor, to be exact.
Course, that was
ten years ago now.
And look at you now,
protecting a nobody!
Oh my, how far the
mighty have fallen!
Let's just say I
stirred up some trouble!
[rapid gunshots]
(unh, unh)
Better say your prayers,
little girl.
You're going straight
to the minister!
(grrr!) That's not gonna happen!
(huh?)
[TATSUMI] (hungh)
(smirks)
(grrr...)
Hurry, Mine! Shoot him!
Tatsumi...
(struggling in background)
I can't believe you'd
sacrifice yourself!
I'm still alive, you know!
You said you're a genius sniper,
didn't you?
You can do it!
(continued struggling)
[INSTRUCTOR]
Damn it, put me down right now!
[TATSUMI] Hurry!
[MINE] Since when do you think
you can give me orders?
Might as well give it
my best shot though!
(wah!) Ah crap!
(powering up whine)
(rapid, heavy breathing)
(ungh)
(chuckles)
(gunshot)
You... You bastards are
gonna pay dearly for...
for assassinating... a member
of the minister's own family...
(blurk)
(gasping for breath)
[MINE] Hey, you. Looks like
you've got some guts after all.
I suppose I ought to commend
you on your braver‐ (ow, ow, ow)
[TATSUMI] You didn't need
to cut it that close.
Look at what that Pumpkin thing
did to my freakin' hair!
Ah! What's with you?!
A genius was about to give
you a compliment, dumbass!
[TATSUMI] Oh, shut it!
You're not a genius,
you're just too smart
for you own good!
I guess there was no need to
(argument continues)
rush all the way over here, was
there?
(hmm)
[ZANKU] Some fellow
Imperial Arms users...
and they're killers!
Mmm, how utterly delightful!
I must get my hands on them.
[GUARD] Hey, you over there!
What're you doing back here?
Don't move!
[ZANKU] I think the Imperial
Capital's going to be
the perfect place
to call my new home.
It's so crowded there's a new
victim around every corner!
(evil chuckle)
How delightful!