[EMPEROR] General Esdeath...
For your success in conquering
the northern tribe,
We have arranged a reward
of 10,000 gold coins.
I'm grateful, Your Highness.
I'll send it to
the soldiers
still fighting to
protect our land.
They will be pleased.
Esdeath truly doesn't care
for money or power.
She is only concerned with
war and victory.
As long as I'm in control,
she can destroy whatever
she wishes.
Our interests can coexist.
She is the ideal puppet.
Now that I've returned to the
capital from the northlands,
Your Majesty can once again
rest at ease.
I shall be terminating
Night Raid next.
Quite an undertaking.
We would like to
compensate you for such
an ambitious achievement
with more than just money.
Is there something else
you'd prefer?
Actually, there is.
If I could choose anything...
[EMPEROR] Go on.
I believe I'd like to
try falling in love.
(huh?)
[MINISTER] (huh?)
Uh, yes, that sounds reasonable!
You ARE a single woman of
marriageable age, after all!
I will serve as your matchmaker!
So what is your opinion
of the minister here?
Huh? Wait, what?!
[ESDEATH] The Minister doesn't
take very good care of himself.
He will not live much longer.
Preposterous!
I'm in perfect health. (chomp!)
Well then, would you be so kind
as to tell us what you'd like?
First, let me warn you that I
can be terribly selective.
Very few men will come close
to my expectations.
Once I'm ready, I will
present you with
an extensive list of
my preferences.
(gritting teeth in pain)
(surprised)
[AKAME] Here.
I don't need you to
spoon‐feed me!
But it'll get cold.
(uh‐)
Okay, I guess you win.
(chomp)
[TATSUMI]
Even after what happened...
Akame's so calm.
I still can't believe it.
I can't believe that
girl killed Sheele.
I'm finally starting
to realize...
how painful this
job really is.
[ESDEATH]
You know, it's strange.
I don't normally take an
interest in anything
besides war and bloodshed.
[MINISTER] Oh, we're talking
about love, I presume?
I don't even understand
this myself,
but I'm feeling a
desperate need for romance.
[MINISTER]
Desire for the opposite sex
is something all
living creatures feel.
I don't know if I'd use the word
"romance" in your case.
It's interesting, yet it's
still an animalistic instinct.
But for the moment, I must
channel all my energy
into eliminating Night Raid.
[MINISTER]
Ah, while we're on the subject.
I've come up with a new idea
that I think you'll like.
I have a special assignment for
you, my precious Three Beasts.
We will do anything you command
us to do, General Esdeath.
Yes ma'am, all of us
are your loyal and devoted
servants forever!
No matter what you wish, we will
carry out any order at any time.
Good.
Man, it's cold.
How am I supposed to
sleep like this?
I'll get some water.
(huh?) Akame?
Late‐night snack?
No, but they were always one
of Sheele's favorites.
It's an offering.
Since our work's always been
done behind the scenes,
Sheele's name probably isn't in
the Revolutionary record books.
So if I don't hold on
to her memory,
then it'll be just like
she was never here.
She might have been
absentminded,
but she was the kindest
person on the team.
(choked up)
[TATSUMI] I agree.
And I see you still
leave flowers
at Sayo and Ieyasu's graves
sometimes too, don't you?
[AKAME] Yeah.
[TATSUMI]
Akame, you're pretty amazing.
[AKAME] (huh?)
You're handling your friend's
death so calmly.
I guess you're used to it.
I still can't‐ (huh?!)
(breaking glass)
You think that I'm...
I'm used to it?
[TATSUMI] Akame? (gurk!)
[AKAME] Sure... maybe
I've witnessed more deaths
than I care to count.
But this...
you don't ever get used to it!
Godammit! You just hide it
and you finish the mission!
[TATSUMI] (gasps)
I have to act like everything
is okay, but on the inside,
I've been falling apart!
(sobbing)
We're assassins, Tatsumi,
we have to be able to
switch things on and off.
You... You think that I'm calm?
(sobbing) Well you're wrong!
You don't know what it's like!
You don't know what
losing her means to me!
You don't know... (sobbing)
I've never seen Akame
break down like this.
I guess I shouldn't
be surprised.
She was pretty worried about
me on my first mission.
(ungh)
What the hell's wrong with me?
Feeling sorry for myself isn't
gonna bring Sheele back!
I just need to move on and
remember why I'm here!
I need to grow up
and just be a man!
(SMACK!)
(gasps)
It's a dirty job,
but money is money,
and I have to keep my village
from starving until the
revolution is over.
I have to do what I can for the
people I care about most!
(thump)
What did you do that for?!
Tatsumi, are you all right?
Yeah, I just needed to get
my head back together.
Don't worry about me.
I also wanna tell you
that I'm sorry.
That was insensitive of me.
And I wanna renew my
pledge to you:
I promise you I won't die
and I won't ever make
you sad again, Akame!
[AKAME] Tatsumi...
We're gonna make it
through to the end.
I want to see
the new nation together!
Yeah. I'd like that.
(hmph)
(ungh, uh)
YAH!
Crap!
(panting)
[TATSUMI]
One more round, all right?
Don't you think you might need
to rest up a little bit first?
[TATSUMI]
I don't have time for that!
Remember, we're pretending
this is a real fight,
so don't hold back!
Here I coooome...
(smack)
(arrrgggh!)
Dammit, Bro, what was that for?!
If you want to pretend
it's for real,
you should pay more attention
to what's around you.
There could always be another
enemy nearby. Understand?
(grrr...)
(chuckles)
Well, somebody seems
a little on edge today.
What's up?
[TATSUMI] Not much.
I just want to level up
as fast as I can.
I have to keep
my promise to Akame!
No matter what happens,
I have to survive!
I hope so...
[TATSUMI] (urk!)
[BULAT] Now that's the kind
of attitude I like to see!
You've come pretty far! Say!
Why don't you try sparring
with me for a little while?
I can whip you into shape!
Sure! Great!
You watch yourself!
I'm pretty good with a spear!
Heads up!
(ungh)
[BULAT]
Is that really all you got?!
[TATSUMI] (waaahhh)
Takes more than passion to
stay alive, you know!
Yeah! Yaaahhh!
[BULAT] Now come at me!
(Hah! Hyah!)
[AKAME] Good luck.
[CHORI]
Yet another devastated village.
A nation is nothing
without its people.
[SPEAR] You really do care,
don't you, Father?
Enough to return to the
snake pit of the capital.
It makes me proud.
This is no time
to cower in retirement
and let life pass me by.
I intend to fight that minister
till my very last breath.
And I intend to watch over you
every step of the way!
I'm lucky to have such
a brave daughter.
Now, if only you wouldn't scare
away all of your suitors.
Wha‐?! Now what does that
have to do with anything?!
(hearty laugh)
(loud disturbance)
What's happening out there?!
More bandits...
This area's getting worse
all the time!
Don't worry, Father.
I'll take care of this!
Everyone, ready!
Daidara...
Yep!
Take 'em out!
(YAAAHHH!!!)
YAH‐HA!
(gasps)
(ungh)
I'm sorry, Father...
[NYAU] Well, you're
a feisty one, aren't cha?
But considering everything
I'm about to do to you,
you're probably gonna wish you'd
been killed already. (giggles)
(waah ‐ ungh)
[CHORI] You...
you're an Imperial officer!
I am, and I once had a deep
respect for your diplomacy, sir.
Then why in God's name would you
do something like this?!
Because my master ordered it.
(snick ‐ sploosh)
And the wishes of my master
shall always be realized.
[DAIDARA] Look at this.
We took out like 15 guys.
Sweet, man! I'm gonna get so
many experience points for this!
Don't forget the notices.
If you ask me, the minister's
idea's a pain in the ass.
Why not pin it on his political
enemies like he usually does?
Because this plan would have
no effect on officials
under the protection of
Great General Budo.
[NYAU] Ah, are we done already?
[DAIDARA]
Nyau, stop screwing around!
[LIVER] You did make sure to
finish her off, didn't you?
(giggles) I was just in the
middle of skinning her face
when she died of shock.
[DAIDARA] You are one
messed‐up kid, you know that?
The mission is now complete.
Let's be on our way.
[NAJENDA]
Now that everyone is here, I'm
afraid I have some bad news.
Esdeath has taken
the northern tribe,
and has now returned to
the Imperial Capital.
(gasps)
Leone I would like you to make
your way to the capital
and figure out what
General Esdeath is up to.
You got it! I've been wondering
what that chick is like!
(sigh)
She's a disturbed psychopath
obsessed with killing.
Don't be careless.
All right, don't worry.
(chuckles)
That means I can waste her if I
get the chance, doesn't it?
I heard that wackjob is
the strongest person
in the empire.
That puts her right up there
with the minister on
our hit list!
Also, ever since her arrival
in the capital,
there's been an increase
in assassinations of
imperial officials.
As of today, four officers
and 61 bodyguards have
been murdered.
What concerns me are
these flyers they've
been scattering around
that claim Night Raid is
responsible for the homicides.
So they're trying to stick
the whole thing on us, huh?
But doesn't this sorta stuff
always get straightened out?
Those posters really don't
look all that legit.
[NAJENDA] That's how most people
felt about it at first.
But now, public opinion is
starting to change.
[TATSUMI] But why?!
[NAJENDA] All of the victims had
first‐rate guards when the
crimes were committed.
They couldn't have been
overpowered by ordinary thugs.
So basically, these guys
are going after the
big fish on purpose.
Only a few people
could pull that off.
That would only be us
or someone equally skilled.
It's safe to assume two things:
They probably have
Imperial Arms,
and they're working for
General Esdeath.
What is she trying
to accomplish?
She's trying to trick us.
She wants to lure us out in the
open so she can strike.
Now that we know it's a trap,
I want to throw one more
thing out there.
The people they're assassinating
are all competent individuals
who disagree with the minister's
policies and recognize the
need for revolution.
After we create the new nation,
allies like them will be
crucial to its success.
(exhales)
To put it simply:
We cannot afford to
continue losing them.
I'd like to hear
everyone's thoughts.
[TATSUMI] Listen...
I don't know very much about
all this political stuff,
but the idea of somebody abusing
Night Raid's name like that
really pisses me off!
Tatsumi...
You know, you're exactly right.
Thanks, man.
[ALL] (uh‐hmm)
Good! That settles it.
Show the bastards what happens
when they use our name.
Night Raid will not be sullied.
There are two of us that
they'll likely target next:
Akame and Lubbock.
Tatsumi and Bulat,
you will guard the person
I assign to you.
Sounds good to me.
Just tell us where to meet him,
and we'll take care
of everything.
Your charge will be boarding
a cruise ship
currently docked at the
grand canal near the
Imperial Capital...
the Ryusen!
[TATSUMI]
It's... IT'S HUUUUUUUGE!!
Looks more like a fortress
than a cruise ship.
Should be an interesting place
to intercept our targets.
[LUBBOCK] Rice reserves, huh?
Must be pretty smart.
[AKAME] All that rice will
make a lot of people happy.
(stomach growls)
I guess I made myself hungry
just looking at it.
(sigh) You can have my rations
if you take out any enemies
that pop up.
We got a deal? (urk!)
[AKAME] (chomp!)
(stretching noises)
[LUBBOCK] No action here.
Looks like we completely
missed the mark this time.
Don't let your guard down yet.
I know, I won't.
Tatsumi... Bulat...
If they're going
after your target...
Please... come back safe!
[TATSUMI]
The guy we're protecting is
surrounded by bodyguards.
There's no way anyone could
even get close to him.
They probably aren't
gonna show up. (urk!)
The hell was that?
[BULAT] Don't be so quick
to assume, Tatsumi.
Wait... Bro?!
[BULAT] My trump card is
invisibility, remember?
And you never know
what our foes might do.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess I didn't think that
through, did I?
How many times would you say
you've smacked me in the head,
by the way?
[BULAT] Eh, sometimes you need
a little tough love.
(echoing) Love... LOVE...
Did you really have to
make it echo?!
Well anyway, I bet this armor is
really cool to have around.
It certainly made it easy
to sneak up onto the ship.
[BULAT] That's right.
Got me through the battle
with the southern tribe.
I kinda like to think
of it as my partner.
However, when it comes to
partnerships,
sometimes things aren't
always so simple.
[BULAT] (ungh)
Sir! I don't understand!
I mean how can they just
discharge you from the capital?!
I couldn't stand the thought
of having to bribe the new
minister, so I refused.
So if you want to move up in
rank, you just have to
give him some money?!
That's bullshit!
[LIVER] Calm yourself, Bulat.
I am going back to the capital
to plead my case.
Despite the position I'm in at
the moment,
I have done nothing wrong.
I am confident that
the court will see that.
[BULAT] General...
It wasn't fair that you were
placed under an officer like me.
I hope you can forgive me.
[BULAT]
Of course... I admire you.
But as you can imagine,
the court didn't end up
ruling in his favor.
And then some people who were
jealous of MY ability
started saying I was a criminal.
I was getting sick of it.
So I used Incursio to escape
before they could catch me.
Man, that's so messed up.
(huh?!)
[BULAT] Looks like my
invisibility's wearing off.
Better remove my armor.
But they know your face
from all the posters.
You can let me handle the
open public areas, okay?
[BULAT] Good thinking!
I'll go check the ship's hold.
I'd better keep an eye out for
anybody who looks suspicious.
Ha! Though I guess I look
pretty suspicious myself.
(flute music begins)
Who's playing a flute?
[ESDEATH]
I'll have your best dessert.
[VENDOR]
Uh yes, comin' right up.
She's sitting right out
in the open.
I can sense it.
This is a trap to
draw us out!
That evil woman!
She's oozing with the
scent of hatred!
I can smell it all over her!
It was stupid of me to think
I could take her out
just because she was
easy to find!
It kills me, but I must follow
my instincts and withdraw.
[ESDEATH] The aura's gone.
I guess they didn't
take the bait.
And I'd hoped to test out
some new torture techniques.
(hmm) My, that's pretty good.
Perhaps I'll treat everyone
when this job is done.
(flute music playing)
Your sweet melody sounds
as elegant as ever.
The cruise ship has left
the Imperial Capital
and no one can see us
from the shore.
It appears the timing
will be perfect.
[NYAU] I've been playing
for a long time now,
so all the passengers should
be nice and drowsy!
There may be people on board
who don't appreciate
the beauty of your music.
You'll have to be wary.
[NYAU] Of course...
[TATSUMI] (ungh)
What the heck is going on?
That flute must be causing this.
(ungh)
I gotta get outside!
(aggghhh)
I can still hear it out here!
It has to be an Imperial Arms.
[DAIDARA] Hey little fella,
it's supposed to be nap time.
And here I was gonna let you
live if you were sleepin'.
[TATSUMI]
You must be one of those Night
Raid posers I've heard about.
(laughing) Does that mean you
think you're the real deal?
This should be good.
Heads up!
[TATSUMI] (huh?!)
Hey, what's the sword for?
Gotta fight fair.
I wanna make sure I get
experience points for this.
Always looking to get stronger.
Come at me, little man!
Uh, fine.
I'll give you some experience.
But it's not gonna be pretty!
Ah, nice!
I like that confidence!
Man, it's gonna be fun
to crush you!
(eek)
(SMASH!)
Heh, heh!
[TATSUMI] (unh)
[DAIDARA]
Amazing you could dodge that
after the music debuff.
[TATSUMI] (breathing heavily)
That's okay.
Let's see how you handle THIS!
(uggghhh)
(uh!)
(nggghhh) Are those things
your Imperial Arms?
Yup! Double Great Axes Belvaac.
Bet a low‐level punk like you
can't even hit it!
(ungh!)
(grrr) In that case...
[DAIDARA] (huh?)
I guess I'll just have to
make it hit YOU!
[DAIDARA] (heh)
TATSUMI, YOU IDIOT!
[TATSUMI] (waaahhh!)
That guy was obviously getting
ready to finish you off
and you just barreled right in
there without even thinking
about it!
You need to learn
to be more responsible!
(ummm...) Hang on!
How do you have so much energy?
The Song of Lethargy was
supposed to put everybody
on the boat to sleep.
So that's what all that
racket was about?
Cheap crap like that
doesn't work on me.
[DAIDARA] What?
[BULAT] If you think playing a
little tune is enough to smother
the burning passion in my soul,
then you've got another
thing coming, my friend!
(huh?) Wait a sec...
Okay, I see what you did there.
You stabbed yourself
so you'd be too distracted
to hear the lullaby.
The name's Bulat of Night Raid.
You can also call me "Handsome".
Yeah, I don't think so, jackass.
I'm Daidara, servant of Esdeath.
[BULAT] Tatsumi...
[TATSUMI] (uh!)
[BULAT] It's very important for
you to pay close attention
to how I fight, okay?
Bro?
(hmph)
INCURSIO!
(swooshing sounds)
I am gonna get a ton of
experience points for this guy!
Behind you!
He's mine! I'm gonna crack
his skull open! (huh?!)
(urk!)
(ungh!)
(uuuhhh...)
(gasps)
[BULAT] See?
(patter of raining blood)
This is what I meant
when I told you
to always be aware
of your surroundings.
He slaughtered the big guy
AND got the other two
off his back.
And... he did it
in a split second!
Whoa, I always knew you were
a good fighter,
but that was awesome!
[BULAT] Damn straight!
Back in my soldier days,
they used to call me
Hundred‐Man Slayer.
[LIVER] I believe it was
a 128, to be exact.
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
You played a vital role
in getting rid
of covert operatives
back then, did you not?
I'd know that power and
that armor anywhere.
It truly has been a while,
hasn't it, Bulat?
[BULAT] (gasps)
It's you...
General Liver!