Tatsumi died
because he was weak.
It's as simple as that.
So then... why...
does it hurt?
[REVOLUTIONARIES]
It's Esdeath!
She's the last of them!
Get her!
The Empire is weak as well...
No, don't!
It must be terminated!
[Screams]
[Panting]
Uh?
Akame.
Looks like you
lose, Esdeath.
No, the Empire lost.
Regardless, my expedition
is far from finished.
Expedition?
But the war is
already over!
There will always
be another war.
If I have to,
I'll start one myself.
This world is poised
on the brink of peace.
And that's exactly
the reason...
I cannot let you
stay alive!
Oh spare me the drama.
If you want to oppose me...
then show me
how much you want it!
[NAJENDA]
Esdeath, you truly are
the final obstacle
to this revolution.
Akame! Annihilate her!
You're dead.
We'll see about that!
[Grunts]
Hahaha...
[Grunt]
Ah!
Hahaha...
Hyaa!
Oh!
Now freeze!
Uh?
Heh...
Now I see where you
get your reputation.
Very good!
Esdeath.
What is it you'll gain from
executing more people?
In the end,
what will be left?
The victors,
of course.
You mean murderers
standing on top of a
mountain of dead bodies.
Am I supposed to feel
remorseful or excited?
If you're not
ready to die,
then surrender and accept
your subordination now.
Never.
Those who can't
win must perish.
That's the way the world
operates, isn't it?
No!
Everyone wants to live.
The ones who died
wanted to live too!
Aah!
Ha!
No one should ever
have the right
to take the life of
another human being!
A rather silly thing to say
coming from an assassin,
don't you think!
Ah!
[Grunting]
Finish her.
Ugh!
Ah!
Hehe... [Snaps her fingers]
Oh!
Ahh!
Ugh!
[ESDEATH]
What's the matter?
Have you had enough?
Aaah!
If you're weak,
then don't challenge me.
And if you don't believe
you can win, don't try.
Swine should grovel in
the dirt like the filthy
livestock they are.
Livestock? Is that all
people are to you?
I cannot concern myself
with the weak.
Ah!
[Labored breathing]
Well? Ready to get
serious yet?
Uh!
Ugh... Uhh...
[Demonic grunting]
Oh! This must be
your trump card.
I've murdered
a lot of people
in my life.
Their grief...
their sorrow...
anger...
hatred.
Everyone I've
ever killed...
Murasame remembers them all.
I'll take the full weight of
that guilt upon myself!
I'm quite impressed!
You've cast off
your human skin!
What a fitting perk
for a demon sword.
Even if it kills me...
I'll end you...
now!
Uh!
Hyaa!
[Struggling]
Err...
Aah!
AAAHH!
Ugh!
[Pained breathing]
Ugh...
Huh?!
[Slice]
[ESDEATH]
Hehe... How about that?
Now it's getting fun!
I can't remember the last time
a fight gave me such a rush!
Alright! It'll be even better
when I tear you to pieces!
Ah!
Hehe...
Ahh...
Hya!
Aah!
[Panting]
[AKAME]
I don't think I can keep
this up for much longer...
Right...
it's now or never!
Prepare yourself to face
the full might of my power.
Come!
Ha!
Ugh...
Heh...
Mahapadma!
This is the first time I've ever
had to re‐use my trump card.
You've done well.
This has been so much fun.
Huh?!
An afterimage?!
Where did she go?
Uh!
You're done!
Uhhh...
Ugh! But how... did you
see through Mahapadma?!
I knew you would try
the same attack you
used to beat Susanoo.
After that,
it was all just
a matter of timing.
How could you
know that?!
The afterimage you saw...
that was your bloodlust.
I used your pride and
your desperate need‐to‐kill
against you.
Mission complete.
[Akame coughs]
Ugh!
[Panting]
[ESDEATH]
Hehehe...
You really are something,
aren't you?
Where's all that strength
of yours come from?
The burden I carry
is extremely heavy.
And because of it,
I've become stronger.
[ESDEATH]
Do you intend to drag
all those souls
around with you for
the rest of your life?
I do.
Well... that sounds foolish...
in any case, you've bested me.
[Gasp]
[Choking]
It's over now.
Huh? Tatsumi!
[AKAME]
Esdeath!
Tatsumi...
from the moment
I laid eyes on you,
all I wanted was
for us to be together.
[AKAME]
You really were
in love with him...
and that was the very thing
you just couldn't understand.
Commander.
Rest in peace.
[Minister panting]
As expected, the wisest man
finds his way in the end!
Now I'll just silently
sneak away somewhere safe...
And put all of this mess
behind me!
[Crash]
Huh?!
[LEONE]
There you are!
If you think I'm gonna
let the nastiest shit‐bag
in the Empire get away,
you're sorely mistaken.
[Panicking]
Somebody help me!
Anyone, please!
You think you're so
freakin' smart, don'tcha?
You think you can
just sneak off huh?!
Stay away!
Uh... What the‐
Huh?!
Oh no...
Hehehe...
Poor girl!
Surprised by the power
of my Imperial Arms?
It's important to keep your
trump card a secret, isn't it?
Muhaha...
The penalty for making me
cower like a fool...
is death!
Uh!
[Gunshots]
Ugh!
I swear, if it's not the
Emperor, it's someone else.
Dealing with stupidity drains
the life right out of me!
[LEONE]
Errr! Hya!
Huh?!
Gah! Ahh!
Haa!
Ow ow oh ow ow oh!
Why... why...
why are you doing this?!
You'd be a killer too
if you'd grown up in
the dump like I did!
But you wouldn't know
about that, would you?!
Haha!
[Gunshots]
Ugh!
[Clicking]
[Snarl]
[Panicking]
[Labored breathing]
Even if you did manage
to break my Imperial Arms...
[Whimpering]
The strength of my spirit
is more than enough...
Aghh!
...to send a bastard
like you to Hell!
Hur‐ahhh!
Hmph!
[LEONE]
Phew, glad that's
outta my system.
So I guess this means
Night Raid is pretty
much finished, huh?
Hm.
Goodbye... my friend.
Huh?
Leone... don't tell me‐
Aw, don't gimme
that look.
Think! I'll get to
see everyone again.
Uh...
Hmm...
There! There's
that little smile.
Goodbye!
[Footsteps fading]
Bye... Leone.
[People celebrating]
[Girls joyfully laughing]
[Men]
Cheers to the revolution!
Finally get to
kiss our lives of
poverty goodbye!
Yeah! You'll never
get rich if you don't
quit bein' a lazy bum!
[DRUNK]
Hahaha! Got that right!
Come on!
[Man]
Hey, Leone!
Wanna knock back
a cold one with us?
Over here, Gramps,
Leone needs a mug!
Leone, it's been
too long since ya‐
Huh?
Where'd she go?
[Crowd mutters]
[EMPEROR]
A beheading.
That should settle it, right?
[NAJENDA]
Right.
[EMPEROR]
Just when you think
a fallen Emperor
has nothing left to do, there's
one final task to be done.
Yes.
If one gives‐in to hysterics...
then we make fools of ourselves.
The final duty...
is die with pride.
[Climbing footsteps]
[EMPEROR]
Please, create a peaceful land
with no more bloodshed.
[NAJENDA]
You have my word.
This is the last drop
of blood to be spilled.
Kurome, I'll do my best to help
everyone in the new world.
I'll help them to be
safe and happy...
I'll do it for both of us.
And I'll do my
absolute best
as the new Minister
of Home Affairs.
This nation will
finally be at peace.
[WAVE]
And, Commander?
Feel free to share some of
that courage with me.
[RUN]
Do you think she's caught up
with Tatsumi by now?
[WAVE]
Ha! I betcha he's still doing
whatever he can to get away!
Hehe...
Well, we should be going.
There's plenty of work waiting
for us when we get back.
[MAYOR]
Why, this is more than we
ever had before!
I can't believe how much
Tatsumi and the others
have been able to send us,
it's changed everything
around here.
And now that things
have settled back down,
maybe Tatsumi, Sayo, and
Ieyasu would be able to
come on back home again.
Um‐hmm.
They shall return as heroes.
We'll welcome them home
with a glorious celebration.
[NAJENDA]
It's amazing what people
can live through.
Uh?
They're already
rebuilding the city.
Boss...
you're okay, right?
Yeah.
But I can't deny
I've shortened my lifespan.
So there's no telling how much
longer my body will hold out.
I'll dedicate my final
days to setting up
the new nation.
It's the least I can
do for these people
as one of
the survivors.
[AKAME]
If anyone can
do it, it's you.
[NAJENDA]
You're planning on
leaving, aren't you?
Yeah.
If you want to
blame me
for all the Revolutionary
Army's despair, I don't mind.
Sorry you got stuck
with such an ugly
role in this.
I'm sure your
new mission will be
just as challenging.
We've lost many things
along the way...
but I'm still glad I
fought with Night Raid.
Thank you for
inviting me...
Najenda.
Yeah.
It has been an honor.
Farewell.
Good luck out there, Akame.
[NARRATOR]
Night Raid.
At the fall of the Empire,
they were remembered as
a violent gang of criminals
who terrorized the Capital.
However, as the
new society grew,
not a single mention of their
existence could be found.
As long as there
is human nature,
so too must there be malice.
As long as there is malice,
so too must there be evil.
Evil beyond salvation.
For those who don't
wield a sword,
these vile demons are
silenced in the darkness.
By a group of elite assassins.
[AKAME]
Somehow, I made it
through to the end.
And gathered the weight
of more souls to carry
for the rest of my life.
Huh?
Killing is all I know.
But I believe...
I believe I can find
my way to a new future.
I'm certain of it.
So no matter where
that future leads,
I will follow this path
to my destiny.
You're done!