[GEBAZE]
Livestock... livestock...
livestock...
All those stupid, miserable
faces, are priceless!
A herd of sheep
to fill my coffers!
I do believe their taxes make
my wine taste even more sweet!
[CHELSEA] Hello, Master.
Good afternoon.
[GEBAZE]
Ooh! Hope you're ready, my dear.
I'll need a nice,
long full‐body rub today.
(urk)
Mission successful.
So what kind of massage
did you have in mind?
[running footsteps]
We're the Jaegers, sir!
We're here to protect you.
We need to search the mansion.
[KUROME] Look at this.
We were too late.
[CHELSEA]
I don't what happened,
but we must've had a leak
somewhere down the line.
The Jaegers walked in on me.
I'm amazed you
made it out safely.
Those guys are a real threat.
[CHELSEA] He had a few cats,
so turned into one and just
acted casual 'til they left.
(phmeow)
So I guess your Imperial Arms
DOES have its uses then.
I'm not sure how I would've
gotten out of a pinch like that.
It's harder for you now, since
they know what you look like.
Feel free to leave missions
like that to me
from now on, okay?
(huh?) Wow, thanks, Chelsea.
Well, while I'm out
saving the day,
you be sure to
guard the house...
like a puppy.
(waaahhh!)
Just when you're being nice,
you turn into a piece of crap!
Oh my god, I hate you!
[CHELSEA] (laughing)
[TATSUMI] Yeah, I remember
when Mine used to say
the same kinda shit to me.
Well, based on what happened,
it would seem the Jaegers might
be starting to hone in on us.
Well, now that they've run out
of Danger Beasts to hunt,
maybe Night Raid is the last
group of enemies they have
left to fight.
But since Tatsumi decided to
take an island vacation
with their leader,
maybe they'll decide
to go easy on us!
(sphhhttt!)
Leave me alone! I was sent there
against my will, remember?!
Sure, you were just alone in
paradise with a beautiful woman.
It's not like I'm totally
jealous of you or anything.
You coulda just left her there.
I mean she is the most dangerous
killer in the Empire.
Boy, am I glad that wasn't me.
Whoo, I sure am lucky.
LUCKY, LUCKY ME!
Don't hurt yourself there, Lubb.
C'mere, Tatsumi, just forget
all about that nasty lady!
[TATSUMI] Squishy squishy...
[NAJENDA] Esdeath was always
a resilient one.
Even if you'd left her,
she would've found a way back.
So forget about
owing her any favors,
because when you go up
against her in combat,
I expect you to do so
with all you've got.
Did you say "always"?
Hold on, Boss,
how old ARE you anyway?
In my mid‐twenties,
if you must know.
[LUBBOCK] (uh... uh...)
Esdeath is actually
a bit younger.
No way! You're only in
your mid‐twenties?!
I thought you were way older!
(grrr...)
[slaps & thumps in background]
Tatsumi, you should know better
than to ask a woman how
old she is.
It's rude.
[squeaky] Yeah, but when you
talked about Sis being fat,
how come you didn't get
your face smashed in?
Hm? What are you talking about?
Food's ready, everyone.
[AKAME] (ah!)
[TATSUMI] Ow!
[ALL] (pleased, happy sounds)
[NAJENDA] I know it's sudden,
but let's have a strategy
meeting after we eat.
It's time to move out.
The Revolution is finally here.
We're ready to take the first
step towards overthrowing this
corrupt government,
once and for all!
Look, we are not with
Night Raid, I swear!
I promise, we only stole
what we needed to eat!
We would never kill anyone!
[SERYU] So you admit
that you were stealing.
I'm afraid once you've been
tainted, you must be
slaughtered.
[KORO] (deep throated growl)
Koro, snack time.
(roar)
[THIEVES] (screams)
Wait, please listen to me!
I never wanted to take anything,
but they threatened to kill me
if I didn't help them!
You gotta believe me!
Please just give me a fair
trial, I'm begging you!
[SERYU]
And yet you helped them anyway.
A crime is still a crime.
Well, there's no reason for my
commander to concern
herself with you.
I will punish you myself
for your poor judgement!
[KORO] (growl)
[SERYU] Justice be served!
[WAVE] Seryu! There you are!
So, what happened to the
thieves you found?
Don't worry, Wave.
I took care of it.
[WAVE] (huh?)
[WAVE] Stop. You just...
executed them, didn't you?
Listen, just because the Jaegers
have special jurisdiction,
it doesn't mean we can
go around murdering people
whenever we wa‐
They weren't Night Raid,
but they were admitted
criminals,
so I removed them from the
population.
Justice was served.
Let's keep working. There's
still so much evil to purge.
(ah!)
[SERYU] C'mon, Koro.
[WAVE] Seryu...
I won't pretend
this is a pretty job,
but I never knew the imperial
capital was this twisted.
This is seriously messed up.
But I must repay
my debt of honor!
All I can do is fulfill
my duty as a soldier.
[NAJENDA] The Revolutionary Army
is rising up!
As such, I would like to take
this opportunity
to explain our first
order of business.
I assume you're all familiar
with the popular religion
among citizens known as
Path of Peace?
They're the one's who believe
a person's good deeds
determine their happiness
and longevity of life.
Oh, yeah! They used to practice
that religion in my village!
In fact, the day I left
for the capital,
the mayor even gave me
a statue of their god.
In the past ten years,
more and more people
have been joining.
Its influence is quite high
in the eastern part
of the capital.
We have reason to believe that
they're taking up arms.
They're looking to launch
a religious rebellion!
[ALL] (huh?)
The plan is for us to use that
to our fullest advantage.
Hey now, wait just a second!
Don't you understand
how many people could die
if there's a religious
rebellion?!
Shouldn't we try to stifle it
or something?!
The capital's let its backwards
government push the people
over the edge.
(exhales) Even if we managed
to stop the rebellion,
then the angry masses would
simply explode somewhere else.
This forsaken empire's already
living out its last days.
Finally.
[TATSUMI]
Do you really think so? (grrr)
You should've at least
let her finish before
you threw a tantrum.
Just think back to
that story we told you
about the rebel tribe and
the hero from the north.
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
[TATSUMI] Didn't Esdeath put
a stop to both of those though?
[LUBBOCK] They failed because
they tried to confront the
empire by themselves.
The powers that be
are pretty capable.
Give 'em a little time,
and they'll snuff out the
Path of Peace rebellion too.
And when they do it,
it won't be pretty.
And that's where the
Revolutionary Army comes in.
We're allied with
a tribe in the west
that's set to begin
their invasion
the moment the religious
uprising starts to move.
When they do, the empire will
be forced to defend itself
on both sides of the border.
But that won't be enough
to bring it down.
So for the finishing blow,
the Revolutionary Army will
stage a riot in the south.
As soon as we march
into the capital,
we'll bring the empire
to its knees.
Now I get it.
We're planning a
three‐way offensive.
The empire has a long history
of underestimating us.
And now, they're grateful
to the Revolution
for gathering all the people
who oppose them into one place.
The Revolutionary Army's
stronghold is located
at the empire's border.
They'll have to break through a
lot of checkpoints along the way
to get to the Imperial Castle.
Lucky for us,
we're already in secret talks
with several of the
castle viceroys.
Many of them used to work
diligently at Central only to
wind up getting relegated.
So they were happy to cooperate.
It should be quite a sight!
Our forces will storm
the capital and claim
castle after castle
without spilling
an ounce of blood.
Of course, the empire will
probably respond
by sending their trump cards:
Great General Budo and
the Royal Guards.
But that'll drain
the palace defenses,
which works in our favor.
Making it the perfect time
to assassinate the
source of all this.
We'll charge into the
Imperial Palace head‐on,
and we'll kill the minister!
Rip the empire apart
from the inside!
The minister's pretty slick,
so I'm sure he'll try
to sneak away
at the very last second.
[LEONE] Not if I can help it!
This is his mess.
And I'll make sure he pays
for it with his face.
We do have debts to pay.
We promised the western tribe
we would return their land
in exchange for
their assistance.
"Return"?
[MINE] Some parts of the
empire's western territory
were originally owned
by foreign tribes.
I know how desperately
they must want that land back.
[TATSUMI] Oh yeah, I forgot.
Half of Mine's blood comes
from a western tribe.
[NAJENDA] After the empire falls
and its laws are abolished,
the people's anger will subside.
And the quicker we can overthrow
the imperial capital,
the less blood
will have to be spilt.
Is that all right with you,
Tatsumi?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry I interrupted you.
Now then...
You should know there's just one
problem with the Path of Peace,
and it's a pretty big one.
[quiet chanting]
[NAJENDA] A man named Bolic
serves as the assistant
to the charismatic figure
they call their lord.
However, he's actually a spy
sent by the minister.
Bolic seeks to take control from
the religion's founder
and prevent the church from
rebelling against the empire.
So here's what I'd
like you to do.
Sneak into the Path of Peace
headquarters and kill Bolic.
He's also been secretly drugging
his followers through their
food, a little at a time,
getting them addicted and
making them into his slaves.
DON'T go easy on him.
So that bastard gets to hop
around from one hot girl
to the next!
And slipping things into
someone's meal
is an unspeakable insult
to the food!
[BOTH] This guy is going down!
Nice enthusiasm, but I think it
might be a little misplaced.
If we don't do something soon,
he's gonna keep drugging
more and more people.
We need to finish this fast.
We can't forget about
the Jaegers either.
As long as they have
Esdeath calling the shots,
they might as well be the
minister's own private army.
We should eliminate them first.
That way we can be sure the
mission runs smoothly.
[All] (uh‐huh)
Right now, the Jaegers are doing
everything in their power
to get their hands on us.
So we need to draw them
out of the capital...
and strike them all down!
[MINE]
Sounds fun! Let's hit those
jerk‐wads with all we've got!
[NAJENDA] If the opportunity
presents itself,
HQ specifically wants us
to kill Bols and Kurome.
You should be able to fight
people you're familiar with,
right, Tatsumi?
Wave was a good guy, and he's
not one of our targets,
so it's not like I have
a reason to hurt him.
But if I know Wave,
he'll do anything
to protect the rest of his team.
So I'll probably have
to face him anyway.
Above all else, I'm an assassin.
I chose this for myself,
and I knew exactly what I was
getting into when I
decided to join.
I'll do what must be done.
I will complete this mission,
even if I have to kill someone
who's not a target!
I won't hold back!
Good!
[CHELSEA] I can feel the resolve
in those eyes of his.
Hopefully, he won't get all
sympathetic for the enemy
and get himself killed.
Wait, what?
Why am I always troubling
myself with Tatsumi?
It's like,
[LUBBOCK]
You think you're so cool!
I can't help but
worry about him.
[LUBBOCK] Did you remember
to zip your pants?
[TATSUMI]
Yeah, take a look and tell me.
[RUN] Commander.
Two unidentified women have been
spotted on the Highroad.
We have reason to suspect
they're Akame and Mine
from Night Raid.
[ESDEATH]
Gather the Jaegers immediately.
[NARRATOR] All people
must one day turn to ash,
so too must nations
fall to ruin.
There are those who seek
to create a new world,
and those who wish to protect
the world they know.
With opposing ideals
and philosophies,
the two forces are drawn by fate
to their inevitable
confrontation.
With deadly armaments
in their hands
and determination
in their hearts,
they march toward
their final battle.
[chains rattling]
[SPY 1] It's the Jaegers.
All six of them, headed east.
[SPY 2] Everything's exactly
as Najenda planned.
[SPY 1]
All right, marg falcon,
get this information
to Night Raid.
[SPY 2] Go.
[screech]
[SPY 2] So the plan is to
murder a leader of the church
and challenge the Jaegers.
They're gonna need all
the luck they can get.
[SPY 1]
I hope you survive, Night Raid!
We need you.
We need you to help set this
world right again.
[NAJENDA] Six of them, huh?
That means they've sent out
the whole team.
Considering how fast
Esdeath tends to move,
even if she has to ask around
a little to find out
where we are,
I bet she'll be here
by tomorrow afternoon.
[screech]
[NAJENDA] All set.
I've just received word from
the revolutionary spies.
As I said before,
try to casually draw attention
to yourselves today.
[BOTH] Roger that.
Aww, yeah! I can't believe
we get to watch the girls
[giggling & splashing]
bounce around in bikinis!
(pervy laugh)
Can you control yourself?
Try to focus, dude.
This is all part of the mission.
What?! Are you crazy?!
Or impotent?!
Neither jackass!
[LEONE] Tatsumi!
We'd like your opinion
about something.
Do you like my suimsuit or
Chelsea's better?
Ooh, careful
how you answer that!
[TATSUMI] (uuuhhh...)
So? Which is it?
Uh, let's see, I, uh...
Would ya look at that,
Su's here!
How ya doin' there, buddy?!
[LEONE]
Aww, he dodged the question.
Why didn't you ask me? I would
have given you an honest,
non‐biased critique and said
BOTH are amazing and beautiful,
and I wanna just touch 'em
and squeeze 'em forever!
Why didn't you ask me?! (urk)
'Cause we already knew what you
would say, dumbass!
She's right. It means nothing
coming from you! Sorry.
[LUBBOCK]
What's that supposed to mean?!
Why does Tatsumi
get all the action?
WHY?!
[LEONE] Why do you think?!
Great, the rest of the team is
having the time of their lives
down there on the beach.
Ah, man, this is bullcrap.
How come they get
to have all the fun?
Are you doing okay, Akame?
Oh, I'm fine.
Guess you're probably thinking
about your sister, aren't you?
[AKAME] Yeah.
I know she'll be coming after me
sooner or later,
so my thoughts are all over
the place right now.
I...
Uh, Mine?
Once your sister is gone,
you'll need to find a way to
remember that you're not alone.
Okay?
You still have us, you know.
You should be grateful for that.
[AKAME] Thanks.
[ESDEATH]
Najenda is still heading east,
and Akame went to the south.
We have witnesses who testify
that the two of them came
to town together
but left separately.
[SERYU] Hey, this is my snack!
You can have a little treat
later.
[BOLS] If they're going east,
they'll reach
the Path of Peace
headquarters in Kyoroku.
If they go south,
they'll be in a city
that supports the
Revolutionary Army.
Either way,
it's very suspicious.
We can cut them off
if we move quickly.
Let's go!
Not so fast, Wave.
Night Raid is well‐known
around the capital.
And they're fully aware
of the wanted posters
around the city.
Our guards have been able
to track them ever since
they showed up.
So, why exactly would they
allow themselves to be seen?
It feels too easy.
Right. That's why I think
it's probably a trap.
They must have
wanted us to see them.
[SERYU] They were trying to get
us out of the castle
so they could defeat us.
[ESDEATH]
That's the way Najenda fights,
with a cool head
and a burning heart.
Are you saying it's too
dangerous to follow her?
Oh, no, she's not getting away.
After playing it safe and
hiding for so long,
Night Raid has finally decided
to come out into the open.
I don't care if it IS a trap.
We'll destroy the trap too!
Seryu, Run,
you help me locate Najenda.
Kurome, Wave, and Bols,
go find Akame.
(excited chuckle)
[ESDEATH] Always be aware
of your surroundings.
If you feel there are too
many of them lying in wait,
you are free to retreat.
Fight hard, but don't resort
to suicide attacks.
These are the last threats
to the capital.
Trap them in a corner
and finish them off!
[ALL] Roger that!
[hoofbeats]
[BOLS] We're about to face
the toughest criminals
in the capital.
Do you think I'll
match up against them?
Yeah, you'll be okay!
I already fought against
a member of Night Raid
once before.
For some reason,
he wouldn't fight back.
But I still got the impression
we were pretty much evenly
matched.
I'm sure we can win
if we work together!
Luckily your weapon is good
for fighting multiple people
at once.
You're gonna be a big help.
[BOLS] I sure hope so.
You're really sweet and
all for saying that, Wave,
but you're probably the most
worthless member of the group.
[WAVE]
What?! Are you trying to tell me
you don't think I have
what it takes?!
Seems pretty obvious.
You won't last five minutes.
Well, you've obviously never
seen me use my Imperial Arms!
Why don't you
show it to me, then!
Oooh, NOW you're asking for it!
[KUROME] So let's see it!
[BOLS]
Please don't argue, you guys.
[WAVE] Hey, look.
What the heck is that?
[KUROME] Some sorta scarecrow?
[BOLS] I think so.
Once again, very suspicious.
Something isn't right here.
[horses whinnying]
[WAVE] Okay, guys,
keep your eyes open.
[MINE] Targets in sight.
I only see three.
Esdeath must have split
the team in half.
I guess she couldn't resist
going after the boss.
The plan seems to be working.
(ah!)
She looks so much like Akame.
You can tell they're related.
Which is exactly why Akame
shouldn't be the one
to kill her.
All I need...
is one clean shot.
[gunshot]
[explosion]
She dodged that?!
That kind of speed
isn't even possible!
[KUROME] (grrr)
Look out!
(waaahhh!)
[SUSANOO] (kyah!)
[BOLS] Wave?!
[NAJENDA] Well, the sniper
may have missed,
but at least we got rid
of one of you.
Oddly enough, that poor
unfortunate fellow wasn't
even on our hit list.
[BOLS] Night Raid?
And the entire team
is together?!
So the other group was a decoy.
[NAJENDA] Kurome and Bols...
You have been selected as prime
targets among the Jaegers.
Get ready to die!
[BOLS] Targets?
I've burned countless
people alive,
[screams of anguish]
so I always knew a reckoning
would come for me one day.
However...
I cannot allow myself to die.
Big Sister!
Hello, Kurome.
I've been dying to see
you again! How nice!
If I kill you myself,
then I can add you to
Yatsufusa's collection.
Now wouldn't that be
just wonderful?
[electrical crackling]
[rumbling]
[TATSUMI] Is this an earthquake?
[rocks falling]
I've improved a lot
since last we met.
Now I can command
any corpse I choose.
[thmp!]
Pretty neat, right?
[low growl]
[ALL] (gasps)
I mean, look at this.
I can even control S‐Class
Danger Beast Desta Ghoul.
[NAJENDA] I took a gamble
on whether Esdeath would
split up her party.
Now I see why she did.
If she's using Yatsufusa,
it'll take more than a little
trap to throw her off.
How fun...
a battle between Imperial Arms.
(grunt)
(grrr)
(ump)
[KUROME] How many do you
think will die? (giggles)