Wait! No don't!
[AKAME] (gasps)
[click]
[large explosion]
[TATSUMI] What the hell?!
Where'd that come from?
[MINE] (ungh)
[TATSUMI] (gasp)
Kurome's gone.
That was quite
a blast wasn't it.
I guess Rubicante
must have exploded.
Without Bols backing me up,
I would've had a much
harder time
trying to hold my own
back there.
Big Sister...
did you make it out alive?
(ungh!)
The meds are wearing off!
[LEONE] (coughing)
That was bad.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'll be all right.
I just wanted to make sure
that you would still be in
commission for later.
But, Leone...
Oh, you know how I am.
I like to show off my amazing
ability to... heal...
(ah!)
Come on now...
You're...
You're okay, right?
(gasps) LEONE!
[BOLS] (labored breathing)
I think I'm clear now.
But I didn't do right
by my guard, did I?
I sure hope Kurome's safe.
[ESDEATH] I'm curious, Bols.
Why do you prepare such a feast
only to excuse yourself
when it's time for dinner?
[BOLS] I...
If I joined you, I'm sure it
would just ruin the meal.
Oh? So you don't want
to show your face?
That makes me even
more curious, you know.
[BOLS] Ah! Commander!
[BOLS] No, please stop!
Is that it? You had me
thinking it was a lot worse.
I must admit I'm
a little disappointed.
[BOLS] Huh?
Nobody's going to bat an eyelash
over something like that.
Now,
let's all have a meal together.
[WAVE]
What took you so long, Bols?
[SERYU] Jeez, Koro, calm down!
I'll feed you in a minute!
[STYLISH]
The wine is quite stylish!
[SERYU]
Bad dog, bad! Koro, please!
[BOLS] I wish...
we COULD all eat together
one more time.
[child‐like sobbing]
[BOLS] Oh no, what is this?!
What are you doing here,
sweetie?
This isn't a safe place to play!
(screams) A MONSTER!!
[BOLS] Oh no, I'm not a monster!
It's okay, please don't cry!
Oh goodness, you're hurt!
Just sit still for me okay?
[GIRL] (screams)
[BOLS] Now, now, be a big girl!
[GIRL] Please don't eat me!
[BOLS]
Now, that's not very nice.
There you go!
It'll be all better
before you know it.
Just leave it alone and
let it heal, okay?
Thank you! I feel much better!
[BOLS] Such a big brave girl.
[GIRL] (happy laughter)
[BOLS] (happy chuckle)
[GIRL] Y'know what?
All those places
you burned down...
[BOLS] (ungh)
[CHELSEA] They're gone forever.
The girl you saw...
she lived in one of
the villages you destroyed
under SUSPICION of aiding
the Revolution.
Of course,
you've slaughtered so many,
I doubt you even
remember faces anymore.
[BOLS] This is it.
The retribution for
what I've done.
The retribution
I've always deserved.
But I...
I can't...
I must go home!
My girls...
are waiting... for me!
My girls... (sobbing)
My girls...
Honestly, that's the most
disturbing thing about
this line of work:
when you feel
your target's pain.
[LUBBOCK] You got a clean kill
before he could run away.
I'm impressed, Chelsea!
[CHELSEA] Hey, Lubb.
Let's go ahead and meet up
with everybody else all right.
Nah, you go on without me.
I'm going to track down Kurome
and finish her off
before she can get
back to Esdeath.
Kurome's already gone
outside my barrier,
but I think I know which
direction she was headed.
You could probably catch her.
But it's way too dangerous!
It's not like you to bite off
more than you can chew!
I don't have a choice.
If we let Kurome
get away this time,
she'll just come right back
with eight more puppets for us.
I cannot let that happen.
Do me a favor and
let the rest of the team
know what I'm up to, okay?
And if you could,
see if you can convince
a couple of the others
to come back me up.
All right, fine.
But don't do anything stupid,
Chelsea.
Of course not. Don't worry.
If Kurome and Esdeath have
already found each other,
I'll come right back.
I promise.
I'll send someone
as soon as I can.
That would be great!
But it's way too dangerous!
It's not like you to bite off
more than you can chew!
[CHELSEA] He's right. I really
have been out of sorts lately.
It's crazy.
C'mon, Chelsea, focus.
It's time to
take care of business!
[CHELSEA] Kurome, you're next.
I swear I'm gonna take you out.
[KUROME] (heavy sigh)
The medication's all worn off.
We agreed to purchase a
hundred young children
from across the country
and train them to be members of
a new assassination squadron,
but this is obviously
much more than that.
[GOZUKI] What's the big deal?
You need to start
with a few extras.
We'll lose dozens of 'em once we
begin the weeding‐out process
anyway.
[BILL] Hmm, yes.
Naturally, the weakest ones
will drop out on their own.
[GOZUKI] Exactly.
I will take the seven most elite
survivors under my wing.
[CHILDREN] (panting)
[CHILD] (screams)
[CHILDREN] (screams)
[GOZUKI] It's always interesting
to see what type of child
is the first to make it out
of the forest alive.
[KUROME] (panting)
Akame, I can't run any farther.
Almost there, Kurome.
Try to keep moving!
[KUROME] (gasps)
No, they're gonna eat us!
Then we'll go this way!
Hold on to me!
Don't be scared!
I won't let anything hurt you.
(uh‐huh)
[BOTH] (running)
[loud growl]
[KUROME] (screams)
Kurome!
(kyah!)
(gasps)
[CREATURE] (roars)
(gyahh!) Don't touch my sister!
(screams)
[AKAME] I must protect Kurome!
[KUROME]
I have to help my big sister!
You both passed the test.
Did you hear that?
It looks like we made it,
Kurome.
Thank you.
Thank you for helping me, Akame.
[BILL] Are you including
those sisters in the seven?
Oh no, I think it's a bad idea
to keep siblings together.
They'll be nothing but trouble
if they start relying on
each other.
[GOZUKI]
Seeing as you're sisters,
we've decided to split you
two up from now on.
Akame, you're with me.
Kurome, you're going
to the capital.
[AKAME] You can't!
Kurome needs to stay with me!
Please don't make me go!
Kurome!
[KUROME] Akame!
[AKAME] NO! KUROME!
[KUROME] (sobbing)
We will now begin
the experimentation.
You may not have all the innate
skills of the Elite Seven,
but these drugs will
make up the difference.
It's only a matter of time
until I create the perfect
assassination squad.
[YOUNG KUROME] (weakly)
When can I see you, Big Sister?
I'm so tired.
Aww, hurry up, I wanna
change my dress already!
Not 'til I'm finished
patching you up.
Um, Leone, are you sure
you'll be all right?
Uh‐huh! Can't you see
how much better I look?
When Lubb gets back, he can use
Cross Tail to sew my arm back on
and I'll be good as new!
[TATSUMI] Uh, did you say
"sew it back on"?!
It's a special combo skill
only Lubb and I can use.
Pretty handy, don't you think?
[TATSUMI] Uhh...
Healing super quickly is
Lionel's trump card!
[roar]
It's called Regenerator!
Well, that's nice I guess.
Although, my precious Susanoo
can regenerate automatically.
Yeah, whatever.
He's still a maid.
Well anyway, it's
a relief to find out
that she's not gonna
lose her arm forever.
Uh, isn't it?
(uh‐hum)
[TATSUMI] (uhhh...)
[MINE] Still, I gotta say,
it's kinda lame
that your trump card
doesn't do any damage.
That's cute, you're just mad
'cause you don't
HAVE a trump card.
[MINE] Pumpkin doesn't NEED
a trump card, thank you.
The greater the threat,
the stronger its power!
Which means it can get me
out of almost anything.
[SUSANOO]
I'm putting on the ointment.
It might sting a little.
[MINE] OW OW OW OW OW OW OW!
It's pretty embarrassing
when you try to act cool
and end up failing, huh, Mine?
I feel your pain.
Don't you dare take pity on me!
Least I can keep my pants on!
You're the loser here, not me!
[door opening] [panting]
Oh, hey there, Lubb!
Listen,
I need to ask you a favor...
It's Chelsea!
[ALL] (huh?)
[KUROME] (sighs)
Natara and Doya are the only
two friends I have left.
I don't think I'll ever be able
to get that many again.
At least my snacks
are really tasty.
[rustling leaves]
[BOLS] Ah, Kurome, it's you!
Thank goodness
you're not injured!
I can't believe
you're still alive.
That was a huge explosion.
[BOLS] The Incendiary Squad
put me through a ritual
that made me resistant to fire.
Well, that's good.
Glad to hear it.
[BOLS]
But I lost my Imperial Arms.
Are you disappointed in me?
(comforting) No.
[CHELSEA] Tatsumi gave me a
rundown of the personalities
and speech patterns
of all the Jaegers.
Looks like he nailed it.
[CHELSEA] She's not even
going for her weapon.
But I should wait
for the right moment.
Akame said she's
using enhancements.
If I attack now, she could flip
out and make things difficult.
I'll play it safe and
wait for a clear opening.
[NAJENDA] I see.
So Chelsea killed Bols.
And then she ran off to
face Kurome by herself?
You guys, I saw the way she
moved whenever I engaged her.
It seems to me like there's a
lot more going on with her
than just a few drugs.
Those people may have
done some stuff to her
that Akame doesn't
even know about.
(gasps)
[MINE] Chelsea might not be
able to do anything to her.
We need to hurry up
with those reinforcements.
[NAJENDA] Akame, Tatsumi,
that's your cue.
I know you haven't had
much time to rest up,
but I need you to find Chelsea
and help her win!
Right, you got it!
You can count on us!
[BOLS] I think we're almost
to a village now.
[KUROME] But there could be
an ambush waiting for us.
[CHELSEA] Hmm, what is this?
I don't know why,
but something about this girl
feels a little off.
And I haven't found any
golden opportunities.
Maybe I should make a break
for it while I still can.
The commander should be coming
back this way eventually.
Let's just play it safe
until she‐ (unngghh)
[BOLS] Oh no!
Are you in pain, Kurome?!
I guess I should've
had more snacks.
[BOLS] Um, what can I do
to make you feel better?
I'm fine.
I just need to eat something.
[BOLS] Poor thing,
you're suffering, aren't you?
I know, I have a trick
that'll stop the pain.
[CHELSEA] See?
Nothing can hurt you ever again.
It's all over.
[KUROME] (aahhh...)
Big... Sister...
[CHELSEA]
Both targets... eliminated.
So the last words to come
out of your mouth
are "Big Sister."
I really do feel bad for you,
but consider it karma for
everyone you murdered.
[VICEROY] Your grades are
exceptional, Chelsea!
I expect great things from you.
[CHELSEA]
Thank you, Your Excellency!
I'll keep doing my best.
Hmm, I'm sure you will.
(sneaky laugh)
I'll use my brains
to get a decent job
and then marry
into lots of money!
[VICEROY]
Well, that is interesting.
[MERCHANT] Please accept this
small gift, Your Excellency.
Perfect,
just leave it there and go.
A bribe? How could you?
[VICEROY] I saw nothing.
[slaves running]
[SLAVE] Keep running!
[VICEROY] That's it, run!
(cackling laughter)
[running & screams]
[VICEROY] (crazed laughter)
[CHELSEA] He's hunting people.
(grrrr) He's... insane!
[CHELSEA] Is there...
anything I can do about it?
[door creaking]
[CHELSEA] What is that?
[GIRL]
Oh, the box in the basement?
That's an Imperial Arms.
It's called Gaia Foundation.
Supposedly, it's been set aside
because no one can use it.
Really? No one could?
[CHELSEA] I feel like...
it's calling to me.
It...
It wants me to use it!
(squish!)
[MAN] The viceroy, he's dead!
[general commotion]
[CHELSEA]
Everyone's happier now.
They're even cheering!
I've made the world
a better place.
If I put my ability to good use,
maybe I can change this
messed‐up world.
I am bringing peace
to this corrupted land.
It's too bad you won't be
around to see it.
[KUROME] HEY!!!
(gasps)
How'd you get my sword?!
It's too bad your trick
didn't work!
I'm in so much pain right now
I'm not sure I can take it!
But my needle insertion
is normally fatal!
[KUROME]
Right after my sister ran away,
the scientists developed an even
more specialized medicine.
It makes my entire body
incredibly strong,
though it does take
a bit of a toll.
Even I didn't know I'd
survive THAT though.
If you want to
kill me for real,
then it looks like
your only two options
are to cut off my head or
pierce me through the heart.
(gasps)
[explosion]
She's not even human anymore!
I need to transform
and get out of here!
[gunshot]
Ah... no...
(painful panting)
It's hard to move.
I'm running out of energy.
Fine.
But if it's the LAST thing I do,
I WILL make sure that girl dies
right here and now!
Earlier she said BOTH targets
had been eliminated.
That means she's the one
who murdered Bols!
Natara! Doya! Get her!
Chop her into little pieces!
[CHELSEA] (running)
(gasps)
[schawk]
[CHELSEA] (unngghh)
[gunshot]
[CHELSEA] (uuuggghhh)
[CHELSEA] So, it was me.
I was the one
who needed to be punished.
I wanted to show you
what I can do.
I wanted you to be proud of me.
Tatsumi...
I wanted to see you smile again.
And I...
I...
(quiet sob)
[heavy rain]
Oh wow, it's really pouring.
Hey, I'm gonna go invisible
and take a good look around
town real quick.
Stay out of trouble.
You just need to check
the status of things.
Yeah.
[TATSUMI] That trail of blood
on the highroad leads all
the way into town.
If they caught Chelsea,
we've gotta go save her!
Then again,
she knows what she's doing.
Maybe we missed each other
and she's already back
at the base.
[TATSUMI] Yeah, I bet that's it.
She wouldn't have done
anything crazy.
Must've been enemy blood.
[low murmuring]
[TATSUMI] What's going on here?
(aahhh...)
(unh...)
(small gasps)