[HUSBAND] I heard a rumor that
people have been seeing
a new type of Danger‐Beast
around here lately.
Be careful. I don't want you
going out by yourself.
I know, dear,
don't you worry about me.
[loud banging on door]
(gasps)
[snarls]
[rapid gun shots]
[munching sounds]
[WOMAN] (quiet panic)
[growls]
No... no please...
don't hurt me!
(screams)
[EMPEROR] Thanks to the Jaegers,
the number of bandits
near the imperial capital
has drastically decreased.
And Night Raid has kept
a low profile as of late.
They must be quite
afraid of you.
We are pleased with your work!
Yes. Once I discover the
location of their new base,
they will be punished.
(mmm) We have the
utmost faith in you.
But sadly,
We haven't found a suitor
who meets your criteria yet.
Though I should mention
the minister here
does have an unmarried son!
I hear HE has potential.
[MINISTER](grunts)
[ESDEATH] Your Highness,
as I stated in my report,
the position has been filled.
You needn't concern
yourself further.
But didn't you tell Us that he
had vanished without a trace?
How can you have a
relationship like that?
[ESDEATH] The pursuit has made
me want him even more.
It seems this love is
unfamiliar to me.
[EMPEROR] (woah...)
Most intriguing!
Not as much as you think,
Your Grace.
You seem to have
rubbed off on the Emperor.
He's been very interested
in romance of late.
I think he's well on his way
to a life of corruption
and debauchery. (laughs)
My plan is to make sure
the Emperor
enjoys the sweetest life
possible.
Just don't allow him to fall
into any bad habits.
Right. Anyway, I have
a favor to ask of you.
[ESDEATH] I'm listening.
A new species of Danger Beast
has appeared around the capital.
I would like you
to get rid of them.
Yes, I know.
I've already started
investigating that for myself.
Until recently,
creatures like these
only lived in forests
and in the mines.
But just days ago, a few forced
their way into a couple's home
and devoured them alive.
I heard that.
They're also said to bear
a resemblance to human beings.
We could have a lot of fun
with these new toys, yes?
Great General Budo has ordered
that they all be destroyed,
but I would love to
examine them.
As you wish.
After hearing how
deadly they are,
I don't think I can
resist hunting them.
I suppose I could catch two
or three for you.
Please forward the reward
money to the soldiers
I have stationed up north.
You truly are a benevolent
leader, aren't you, General?
A soldier is more likely
to fight to the death
for a commander he respects.
And when you consider
that idea,
it's easy to see why my forces
are considered the strongest
in the nation.
[MINISTER] That's comforting.
Please pick out a few
feisty ones for me.
[rattling wagon wheels]
[TRAVELER] Hurry up!
We need to reach
the capital before dark.
I know, I know, I'm trying to.
We gotta get outta this area
as soon as we possibly can!
(horse whinies in terror)
(gasps)
[TRAVELERS] What's that?!
‐ Oh, my God!
[snarls and growls]
[TRAVELERS] (screams)
[BOLS] Just in time.
[snarling]
[BOLS]
Now then, I'd better clean up.
[pained snarls]
[BOLS] Gentlemen,
is everybody all right?
(gasps and panic)
[BOLS] Um, I went ahead and took
out the Danger Beasts for ya.
So there's no need
to be afraid.
[echoing] ...be afraid...
be afraid... BE AFRAID.
[TRAVELERS] (panicking)
Worry not citizens, you're safe.
They've been incinerated by
the flames of justice!
Oh, thank you!
You must be imperial officers
from the capital, right?
We owe you one!
So uh, that was
kinda awkward, huh?
You did a good thing, okay?
[BOLS] Those... people...
They can feel safe now!
Which is wonderful!
Right?
[panting]
[sudden wind howling]
[ESDEATH] There we go.
Freezing these creatures was
the most effective way of
capturing them.
It's true. I've never seen this
kind of Danger Beast before.
(hungry sounds)
It's not a snack.
[KUROME] (urk)
[BOLS]
Wave, Kurome, the tea is ready.
Oh thanks, Bols.
Uh, thank you for always
waiting on us.
[BOLS] No, no, don't mention it!
I like being helpful.
[BOLS] What's the matter, Wave?
It still just
kind of bothers me.
I mean, you're a
really nice person.
But even when you killed
the Danger Beasts and saved
those guys' lives,
they still judged you
based on how you look!
[KUROME] Yeah, but you
did the same thing.
[WAVE] (huh?)
(gyaaahhh) Crap, I did!
[BOLS] Wave, I told you before.
I'm not a... nice person.
I've been to inflicted
and diseased villages,
and I've burned them
to the ground.
I was an executioner.
I've burned innocent men
and women to ashes.
I've done so many
horrible things.
I've lost count of the names
of those who want me dead.
But all you did was follow
the orders you were
given, right?!
[BOLS]
What I do may just be a job,
but karma is still karma.
I figure I'm only
getting what I deserve:
reminders, retribution.
But Bols, you shouldn't torture
yourself like that!
Listen, if you ever need
a shoulder to cry on,
I'm right here okay!
[KIJE] Honey!
[ROGUE] (giggles) Daddy!
[WAVE] Huh?
[BOLS] My girls!
[BOLS] What are you lovely
ladies doing here?
You big 'ol goofball,
you left your lunch
sitting on the kitchen counter
this morning.
[BOLS] Oh, my GOODNESS!
Mommy, Daddy made a boo‐boo!
[All] (laughing)
You have such a demanding job,
sweetie.
If you don't eat lunch,
you might get too light‐headed.
[BOLS] Yes, dear.
I'll be more careful next time.
Daddy! Hold me!
[BOLS]
All right, c'mere, big girl!
[ROGUE] (laughing)
[BOLS] Look, I appreciate
your concern, Wave.
But my wife and my daughter know
all about the things I do,
and well, they still
love me, no matter what.
It's because of them that,
y'know...
[ROUGE] (giggles)
That nothing out there is too
much for me.
[WAVE] (ungghhh)
[WAVE] God,
I can't even stand it!
[BOLS] (chuckling)
Turn down the love!
Oh man, I think this is
twice in a row
I've failed at
comforting someone?
[ALL] (happy laughs)
[KIJE] Aww, daddy's little girl!
[water rushing]
[TATSUMI] (hyaaahhh)
Do not rely
on simple brute force
when you try to hit something.
[TATSUMI] (huh?!)
[SUSANOO] (umph)
No matter how resilient
your opponent may seem,
there's always a weak spot
somewhere.
[TATSUMI] Whoa...
Try to remember that the next
time you're in battle
so you can disarm your enemy.
[TATSUMI] Yeah, I will.
But wait, do you think
I'll be able to pull off
something like that
in the middle of a fight?
[SUSANOO] It always seems to
present itself eventually.
You must be pretty observant
then, huh, Su?
Something like that.
I was originally created
to look after my master.
I have been trained to observe
every little detail around me.
Makes sense to me!
Well, it's great
to have you around!
Y'know since you came along,
I've been a lot more confident
that all eight of us
are gonna live to see
the end of this whole thing.
I am an Imperial Arms.
There's no need for you
to include me in such things.
[TATSUMI] Don't say that!
You're a weapon AND a companion!
Companion? Why?
I'm not really sure
I understand.
That word refers to people who
fight alongside one another.
Wha‐? Yeah, well that too,
but it's a lot more than that.
Umm...
Companions...
just help each other out.
Hey, I got it!
You're a relatively
handsome guy.
When all this fighting's over,
I want you
to help me and Lubb
pick up chicks.
How's that sound?
(hmph) Not sure if I know how.
But if that really is what
you want from me,
I'll do everything in my power
to help you achieve it.
Aw, yeah!
[AKAME] Hey, Su! Tatsumi!
[TATSUMI] (huh)
The boss just called an
emergency meeting.
We need to get back to base.
Emergency? What's going on?
Apparently, some new
Danger Beasts
are causing a lot of trouble
in the imperial capital.
But before we can
take care of them,
we're relocating
to our new hideout.
[TATSUMI] (huh)
The Capital, huh?
This is it?
It doesn't look any different
from the old hideout.
Well, when you build a facility
that's hard to find and
easy to flee,
it pretty much looks like this.
And the best part is the new one
has a hot spring, too!
After this job, we should have
a soak and get trashed!
Sounds like fun!
[LUBBOCK] Najenda, guess what!
I set up a barrier
all the way around
the perimeter of the hideout!
Okay.
And I dug out a few traps
in case of an emergency.
Oh, that was really fast,
Susanoo. Nice work!
[LUBBOCK] (urk!)
(angry growl)
You'd better
watch yourself, pal!
Hm? What are you talking about?
[TATSUMI] (sigh)
[NAJENDA] I hate to send
you all out again so soon,
but your next job is to take out
the Danger Beasts I mentioned.
We don't know very much
about them at the moment,
except that they're
somewhat intelligent
and they usually like
to travel in packs.
But individually,
they're still extremely strong.
They've overpowered everyone
who's tried to fight them.
They've been attacking both
humans and livestock
south of the capital
in various environments,
from mines to forests.
The Jaegers and
the Imperial Army
are working day in and day out
to exterminate them,
but their numbers
haven't decreased much.
If they're giving
the Empire a hard time,
then I seriously doubt
this is a trap.
(exhales) Undoubtedly,
we're actually HELPING the
Empire by taking this job.
Can you live with that?
Absolutely, Boss!
After all,
this is a special case.
I agree with Tatsumi.
It sounds like we should
defeat them as soon as possible.
I just hope we don't run into
any Imperial Soldiers
while we're near the capital.
(hmm?) Shouldn't be an issue.
We're Night Raid. We do our work
while the soldiers are off duty.
Oh yeah, guess so.
[CHELSEA] (sigh)
So you bleeding hearts will
just put yourselves in danger
just to help slay the monsters?
Leave it to the Jaegers
to get themselves killed.
You guys really have to stop
being so soft all the time.
(troubled sigh)
[TATSUMI] I understand
where you're coming from.
[CHELSEA] (huh?)
[TATSUMI] But what if those
things are killing more
innocent people as we speak?
Even if we are
a bunch of assassins,
we're still allies
of the people!
And if we really want to help,
we have to kill those things
right now!
[CHELSEA] I figured you'd say
something like that.
(sighs) Fine, you win.
(mmm)
(aggghh)
[SUSANOO] Tatsumi...
There's something
I really need to tell you.
[TATSUMI] What's that?
Could you please
zip up your pants?
It's been bothering me
for a while now.
(aaaggghhh)
[LEONE & LUBBOCK] (laughing)
So much for trying to
look all cool, Romeo!
[LUBBOCK]
Yeah, Tatsumi, you're the man!
We totally take you seriously!
[LEONE] (laughing)
You're awesome. So smooth.
It serves you right, loser.
[LUBBOCK] Mr. Cool.
Come on, guys!
[AKAME] Sorry, Tatsumi.
I noticed it a while ago, but I
thought it might be intentional.
Are you crazy?! What the hell
kind of exhibitionist
do you think I am?!
[AKAME] (ummm)
[TATSUMI] (urk)
From now on, I'll watch closely
to ensure it stays up.
[TATSUMI] (waaaahh!)
No thanks,
I'm sure I'll be fine!
It's an ingenious technique. A
great way to distract the enemy.
You need to
shut your stupid face!
Oh, there's nothing to
be embarrassed about.
[TATSUMI] I swear I am going
to kill you, Lubbock.
You had your fly down
for the people, right?
[TATSUMI]
I am going to kill you dead.
Huh?! Seriously?
[LUBBOCK] Ha, ha!
This is actually pretty
normal for our crowd.
[commotion in background]
Make sure you're prepared
for plenty of headaches.
Yeah, I'm prepared for that,
but I'm a little scared.
I mean I can't help
but be worried
after reading about
Sheele and Bulat.
Tatsumi's too nice,
like they were.
I'm afraid it's
gonna get him killed.
[commotion continues]
[LUBBOCK]
Awww, don't be such a baby!
[ESDEATH]
Run, I have something very
important to discuss with you.
Based on the
minister's research,
those Danger Beasts were
once people.
I knew it.
Their physiques did seem
unusually human as I recall.
Someone was turning them
into monsters.
Only an Imperial Arms user could
manage something like that.
There's a distinct possibility
that these new Danger Beasts
could have been the
doctor's experiments.
It's probably not a coincidence
they started wreaking havoc
right about the same time
the doctor disappeared.
Is there more evidence?
When I went to investigate
the laboratory,
I remember noticing that the
place seemed surprisingly empty.
Especially knowing he was almost
always conducting experiments,
I thought it rather odd.
So that means he must have
had another secret lab
somewhere, right?
Yes, and whatever he was
keeping locked up in there
somehow found a way to escape
after he was gone.
It could also be
an unknown third party
stole his Imperial Arms
to make the monsters,
but then again the attacks
seem so random.
I guess it's possible the doctor
stumbled upon the enemy
while he was out
looking for Tatsumi.
He found their hideout
and tried to capture them
and turn them into
his test subjects,
only to have the tables turned
and be killed by them instead.
I'm beginning to think that he
may have been more insane
than I ever thought he was.
If the doctor really was the one
who created those Danger Beasts,
then there should only be
a limited number.
Eventually, the problem
should resolve itself.
[ESDEATH]
There's more to this than how
many we're dealing with.
[RUN] (huh?)
[ESDEATH] For starters, were
those monsters truly capable
of escaping on their own?
Or should we assume that
somebody WANTED to
set them free?
(ah!)
[RUN]
Understood. I will continue
to evaluate the situation
as thoroughly as possible.
[ESDEATH] I'm counting on you.
We don't know exactly how
serious this is yet.
All that aside...
It's unusual to see you stopping
to admire the flowers like this.
[ESDEATH] Hm? Oh, these?
Well, when you rub these
particular flowers into
an open wound,
they cause excruciating pain.
[screams of agony]
I use them in light torture.
[RUN]
I'll be sure to remember that.
How dare you terrorize the good
people of this land?!
[snarls & growls]
Koro, Phase One!
Woof! (growl)
Purifying Ball of Justice!
Koro! They should be all nice
and tender and ready to eat!
[KORO] (growl)
[wet munching sounds]
[SYURA]
That's one of those Jaegers
everybody's talking about.
Living up to their reputation.
[SERYU] Aww, who's a good boy?
You're good boy!
[SYURA] (evil chuckle)
I think I'll play with my toys
just a bit longer.
Man, how did I get paired up
with a dude again?
It's not like we're out here
to get some kissy time,
ya ding dong.
[LUBBOCK]
We should be on the lookout.
There might be
Imperial Soldiers.
Why are you acting so jumpy?
Now, listen here.
It's crucial for an assassin to
be a little bit paranoid.
It helps you stay alert.
[TATSUMI] Uh, ah, hey...
Najenda said that herself,
thank you very much.
You might wanna try it, too!
Now wait a minute, I've noticed
you doing that before.
Hm? You noticed what?
Everybody else just
calls her "Boss,"
but you always
call her Najenda.
Don't you, Lubb?
[LUBBOCK]
Uh... Uh, yeah, I guess I do.
She and I go way back,
all the way back to when she was
fighting in the Imperial Army.
[LUBBOCK] I was the fourth son
of a rich merchant who lived
in the countryside.
I mean I had all I ever wanted
when I was a kid.
I was the best at
everything I did,
so the world seemed
really boring.
Wow, Lubb, sounds to me like
you really had it rough.
[LUBBOCK] It's gonna be a
tearjerker, okay, so shut up!
[LUBBOCK] So one day, Najenda
ends up getting assigned
to the town where I live.
(wow...)
It was love at first sight.
So, of course,
I decided to join the army.
I did whatever it took to climb
the ranks and get closer to her.
So if you used to be
in the army,
then what are you doing
in Night Raid?
Everything I've done
is to be with her...
With Najenda.
When she left the Empire,
I forged my records
to say I was dead
so I could go with her.
Pretty awesome of me.
Don't you think so?
Well anyway,
she doesn't feel the same.
It's unrequited love.
Told you it was gonna
be a tearjerker.
Lubb, awww.
But if you wanna win her love,
you have to stop looking at
other girls in the hot spring!
WHAAAT?! Checking out hot chicks
and being in love
are two totally
different things!
What's the hell's
wrong with you?!
[TATSUMI] See, that's why
she doesn't love you back!
[LUBBOCK] You don't know!
Just you wait, she's gonna
come around one day.
If that ever happens, I'll treat
you to anything you want.
[LUBBOCK]
I look forward to it.
[TATSUMI]
Anyway, I still haven't seen
any Danger Beasts around here.
Do you think maybe there
aren't any left up here
on the mountain?
[LUBBOCK] I set some tripwires,
but it doesn't look like
anything's tripped 'em so far.
[TATSUMI] All right...
Well, if we're sure
this area's okay,
then I guess I should
probably take a look
at the peak real quick.
Remember if you see anything,
just run.
We can fight it together.
[TATSUMI] Sure thing!
[swoosh!]
[TATSUMI]
Nothing really stands out.
I don't even see any animals.
Even Danger Beasts have to go to
sleep sometime, huh?
[ESDEATH]
I know that technically
I'm out here on night patrol,
but I can't help notice how
beautiful it is tonight.
This kind of frivolous nonsense
normally doesn't suit me.
Oh, Tatsumi,
I'm just not myself lately.
And I have you to blame,
my love.
Is that a Danger Beast
down there?
[happy chuckle]
If so, it has terrible luck.
And here I was, starting to
feel sorry for myself.
[ka‐boom!]
[TATSUMI] (ungh)
What the‐
Tonight isn't your night.
I've got a new form of torture
I've been‐ (gasps)
[ESDEATH] Tatsumi?!
[TATSUMI] What's Esdeath doing
here?! This is crazy.
How am I supposed to know
if she's gonna fall
right out of the sky?!
What do I do, what do I do,
what do I do, what do I do?!
[sinister snarls]
Great, this is NOT
what I need right now!
No wait, they look pretty tough.
Maybe I can run away
and leave this to her!
[schnick!]
Then again, maybe not.
There goes that idea.
[snarling]
[ESDEATH] You are in my way.
[TATSUMI] (urk!)
Is this some sort of dream?
I've been waiting so long
for the moment we could
meet again, Tatsumi!
[TATSUMI] Nope, unfortunately
this is not a dream.
So uh, is she gonna finish
that thing off or what?