Kurome...
Unlike you,
I chose to be a soldier.
It was my dream.
There was an officer
who helped me,
and I wanted to be
just like him.
Soldiers fight for what's right.
They're supposed to work hard
to protect their country
and their people.
But now that I am a soldier...
I don't...
I don't have any idea what
I'm protecting anymore.
Looks like it's down
to the four of us.
This place feels really big now.
Yeah, it does.
So, what're we doing after this?
[TATSUMI] (yelps)
After the revolution's over,
there won't be much work
for guys like us, y'know.
If I recall correctly,
when I got here
you practically forced me to
join the team. Remember that?
And when I did, before I
knew it, everything had
gotten all crazy.
Aw, I'm sorry sweetie.
Oh well, then I guess you'll
just have to punish me
with a spanking! (laughs)
No, thank you! Besides,
assassins being out of work
means the world
is a better place!
I guess so.
Well, maybe we could start
a traveling circus group
or something.
Sounds good.
[TATSUMI] No, it doesn't!
I appreciate all you've done
for the cause, team.
Whoa! That sounded way too much
like a final goodbye, Boss!
I don't know whether
we'll meet again.
That's completely up to you.
What're you talking about?
You're gonna have a hell
of a time getting rid
of these three misfits!
Am I right?!
Of course!
You know I'm in!
Good! Then this will be
Night Raid's last assignment:
Cut down the source of
this corruption,
assassinate Minister Honest!
You have to survive.
I will.
You have my word on it.
[loud crash]
[NAJENDA]
Tatsumi, your time limit depends
on how long our main
forces can hold out.
Kill the minister as fast as
you can!
Today we turn our dreams of
revolution into reality,
and pave the way
for a new world!
By the strength of our hearts,
we will abolish this
debauched government,
and its people will
finally live in peace!
[soldiers cheering]
I'm counting on you.
[LEONE] (yaaahhh!)
[explosion]
Bingo! Hardly any guards here,
just like we thought.
[TATSUMI]
Lubb's map was exactly right.
[LEONE] Thanks, little man!
[SOLDIERS] (urk) (ungh)
[SOLDIER] Night Raid!
I don't want to kill
any more than I have to.
Get out or get ready to die.
[SOLDIER] We will not retreat!
Shoulda known they would
keep the toughest ones
reserved to the palace.
[TATSUMI] I guess killing them's
the only way through.
[RUN] None of you can cut it
against Night Raid.
Please fall back now.
[AKAME] One of the Jaegers.
[TATSUMI] It's Run.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I'm surprised you remember me,
Tatsumi.
By any chance, you think
you could let us pass?
Pretty please?
Oh, sorry. I've always been
the type of person
who prefers to finish
everything I start.
[TATSUMI]
Yeah? Even if it's a mistake?
[RUN]
History will ultimately decide
who made the right decision
in a situation like this.
There's no reason to
throw your lives away.
You may leave.
[SOLDIER] Huh?
You can't help me.
As a matter of fact...
you'd be in the way.
Watch out!
Those must be his Imperial Arms!
[RUN] You were right, y'know.
Just as you thought,
the empire as we know it
has become rotten to its core.
The current regime is on
the verge of collapse.
[TATSUMI]
If you know that, why are
you getting in our way?
Because your methods of revolt
cause too much bloodshed.
Are you saying you're no
different?
Well, you see,
I was once a teacher.
How did a teacher
wind up in the Jaegers?!
[RUN]
Not long ago, a group of bandits
abducted my students
and murdered them.
[TATSUMI] (gasps)
[RUN]
But the government didn't treat
it like a crime in any way.
Now, the village I came
from was quite poor,
so the bureaucrats saw
no reason to get involved.
[TATSUMI]
Really? That happened to you?
It did. And it's precisely the
reason I despise this empire.
In that case, why are you
not on OUR side?!
That's where you belong!
My plan was to
infiltrate the Jaegers.
I thought I'd be able to
accomplish more from
the inside!
But Night Raid decided to
resort to violence in the
name of REVOLUTION!
Man, you piss me off!
I'm gonna knock some sense
into your thick skull!
[rumbling]
[LEONE]
Keep moving, you two. I'll
handle this guy on my own!
[TATSUMI] Sis!
It's not a good idea for us all
to be together in one place!
I'm fine, just GO!
Don't you go dying on me.
Not until I get at least
one good hit on the minister,
all right?!
And AS for YOU, this is
gonna be over real quick!
It's nothing personal, but your
ass was doomed when you chose
to fight for the empire!
You chose the wrong side!
(kyaaahhh!)
[LEONE] What the hell?!
Divine Wings, my trump card.
You didn't actually expect
me to fight you in
hand‐to‐hand combat?
[LEONE] Oh, crap...
[EMPEROR]
What's the status, Minister?
[MINISTER]
Doesn't look promising.
I hate to be the
bearer of bad news,
but our forces seem to be
completely overwhelmed
by the onslaught from the
Revolutionary Army.
So we're losing...
I fear Our reign's been
nothing but failure!
Nonsense! Even in the wake of
the unfortunate passing of
your DEAR parents,
Your Majesty has always
been steadfast.
And with me guiding your hand,
at what point could you possibly
have made any mistakes?
Oh yes, you're absolutely right.
You have been a wonderful
example, Minister.
(soft sinister chuckle)
The citizens are losing their
minds over a foolish dream!
The revolution they imagine
will never come to pass!
It's your duty to teach
the defectors a lesson!
I'm sure there will
be casualties,
BUT there are times when a
leader must make sacrifices!
A display of authority
is the remedy for this
absurd rebellion!
Make it so, O Wise One!
[loud crash & screaming]
[TATSUMI] Well, well,
what do we have here?
It's the rebels!
That man's from Night Raid!
How did you get past
the Royal Guards?!
[breaking glass]
Looks like your precious guards
decided to give up.
(waaahhh)
Minister, you're my target.
You're done!
(yaaahhh!)
(cackling laughter)
You're too late!
The ultimate Imperial Arms
has been activated!
You lose! (belch)
[MINISTER] Excuse me...
This empire is
coming to an end,
because of what YOU started!
[TATSUMI]
No! Please, listen to me!
Things were messed up
far longer than that!
The weak and the poor have been
suffering under this tyranny
for ages.
And no matter how hard those
people prayed for things
to change,
you never did anything
to help 'em!
Sayo, Ieyasu, and my friends...
they're all dead now!
This callous nation cannot
stand any longer!
[MINISTER] Your Majesty,
you mustn't allow him to
deceive you! Please!
[TATSUMI]
You hold your tongue, Minister!
Your days of manipulating
the emperor are over!
What? You should stop making
such vile accusations in
royal company.
I give advice out of
love and respect!
[TATSUMI]
That's bullshit and you know it!
Can't you hear what's
happening outside?
The capital IS finished!
Careful, boy...
I'd advise you to
shut your mouth.
Please, Your Highness!
Crush these traitors in
the name of the empire!
[EMPEROR] Submit before
your all‐powerful Emperor!
[low rumbling]
[TATSUMI] What's happening?!
[loud crashes]
The empire's secret weapon,
Primus Imperator!
A machine that's as colossal
and undefeatable as the
gods themselves!
[MINISTER] Now the infidels
who dared defy the empire
will face its wrath!
[MAN] Oh God, what is that?!
[WOMAN] Oh, no!
[MAN] What's going on?!
That thing's enormous!
He's using the legendary
Imperial Arms!
[LEONE] Hey, wait!
Primus Imperator?
So it actually existed?!
Damn that minister!
No wonder he didn't
admit defeat.
He had this up his sleeve
the whole time!
[EMPEROR]
For generations, Our empire
has been a flawless image
of divine order.
And anyone who should rebel
against it must atone
for their SINS!
[tchzang]
[explosions]
STOP IT!
[MINISTER] Oh, how magnificent
you've become, Your Majesty!
Had your mother and father
not been taken by an
inexplicable accident,
they would be so proud!
[EMPEROR] Yes...
[MINISTER] Only those of royal
blood are capable of using
Primus Imperator.
There can be no denying the fact
that you are indeed the
chosen emperor!
This is true.
We are rightful heirs
to this nation.
Yes, Your Grace! Yes! Yes! Yes!
(screams)
[tchzang]
[large explosion]
So this is the weapon
Stylish described
as the first and strongest
of all Imperial Arms.
(panting)
This... is for the best.
[MINISTER] THERE'S a good lad!
(wild laughter)
With this power at your
disposal,
everything around you is yours
to do with as you please!
What's a little destruction in
the quest for absolute power?
The losses can always be purged
from the peasants again!
It's just me and
the emperor now!
(evil laughter)
These guys are tough!
But I guess they are
the emperor's guards.
Tatsumi?!
[TATSUMI] Stop! Look what you're
doing to your own people!
Night Raid has done this.
This is merely the result
of what you've created!
[TATSUMI]
Don't you have any compassion?!
What kind of emperor would be
able to unleash such suffering?!
Silence! This empire is
a thousand years old.
We will never allow it to
collapse during Our reign!
[MINISTER] Hear, hear!
Well said, Your Majesty!
[TATSUMI] The last thousand
years have led to this day!
(hyah!)
[EMPEROR]
As the ruler of this country,
we were born into a life of
crushing responsibilty!
[TATSUMI] (waaahhh)
You could never understand
how that feels!
[TATSUMI] It's bigger than you.
It's bigger than all of us.
[MOM & DAUGHTER] (aahhh...)
It's the anguish and agony
of everyone around you!
[tchzang]
[large explosion]
[TATSUMI]
Look! Can't you see it?!
Can't you see what's happening
down there!
(ah!)
(gasps)
He lies!
Don't listen to such deceit!
If you bow and show leniency,
everything will have
been for naught!
It's time to be strong!
Oh... guess that could
be what we need.
[TATSUMI] What're you doing? I
never said you could look away!
[tchzang]
[huge impact]
[SOLDIER] Your Majesty!
[screaming]
(panting)
[TATSUMI] If you have
the power to do all this,
why not use it to fight the
real problems out there?!
[EMPEROR] Shut up.
[TATSUMI]
Are you just gonna be his little
puppet forever, is that it?
[EMPEROR] SHUT UUUUUP!
[huge thump]
[TATSUMI] (gasps) Wave?!
[WAVE] I'm an Imperial Soldier.
It's my job to protect people!
Man, am I happy to hear that!
(chuckles) And besides, I
already owed you a favor anyway.
Or don't you remember?
[TATSUMI] Huh? A favor?
[WAVE] Don't worry about it.
Your Majesty, calm yourself!
Please!
[EMPEROR]
This crusade is Our cause!
We must see it through
to the end!
[tchzang]
[large explosion]
[WAVE] He has to be
stopped at all costs.
And you and I are the
only ones who can do it!
[TATSUMI]
Yeah, you don't have to tell me!
Infidels! Why do you fight
against your country
AND your Emperor?!
[WAVE]
Don't try to twist what this is!
It's not like I'm siding
with the rebels.
But a soldier is supposed
to protect the innocent.
And that's what I'm gonna do!
[general commotion]
[LEONE]
He sounds like a handful.
Yes, he is.
[LEONE] Hmm?
But we could use
more people like him.
[tchzang] [explosion]
[screams]
We can postpone our little
scrap, right, Fly Boy?
That won't be necessary.
(chuckles)
[TATSUMI] Hyah! Nothing!
[WAVE] Kyah!
Grand Chariot can't
even hurt it!
[tchzang] [tchzang]
We have to keep fighting!
The second we give in,
we lose!
[huge explosion]
(unngghh!)
What was that?!
[WAVE] Look out!
That felt different somehow.
No matter how resilient
your opponent may seem,
there's always
a weak spot somewhere.
Try to remember that
next time you're in battle
so you can disarm your enemy.
Su...
Wave! Make me an opening!
[WAVE] Got it!
This traitor must be executed!
[EMPEROR] (panting)
For betraying the emperor,
you are sentenced to DEATH!
[large explosion]
[TATSUMI] Hyaaahhh!
[EMPEROR] (screams)
[TATSUMI] This is the only place
that seems worn down!
It's just like you said!
There's gotta be a weak spot
somewhere, right, Su?
Nothing's invincible!
DAMN YOU!
[tchzang]
[TATSUMI] (screams)
[WAVE] Tatsumi! (ungh!)
Just give up!
Why do you have to be
so persistent?
We're begging you, please...
please surrender!
[TATSUMI]
Don't underestimate me!
I've been through more pain
than you can imagine!
I carry the hopes of all my
friends who've gone before me,
and I won't allow their
deaths to be in vain!
[BULAT] There will always be
hardships and misery, Tatsumi.
In fact, that's all we get.
But this is the path
we chose for ourselves.
[TATSUMI] Bro?
[BULAT] We should feel fortunate
to do what no one else will.
It's how the world is changed.
And then, we simply disappear.
[TATSUMI] Bro!
Come on and scream!
With all the fire in your soul!
[TATSUMI] Yaaahhh...
INCURSIO!
(determined roar)
The ancient soul inside the
armor is causing it to evolve!
[tchzang]
[huge explosion]
[EMPEROR] Stay back...
Yaaahhh!!
[tchzang]
[TATSUMI] Kyaaahhh!
GET AWAY FROM ME!
[TATSUMI] Yaaahhh!!
(agonized scream)
[TATSUMI] Kyaaahhh!
[WAVE]
Are you trying to get killed?!
Of course I'm not!
I made a promise, didn't I?!
I swore I'd make it back alive!
TATSUMI!
[TATSUMI] KYAAAHHH!!!
(gasps)
[sharp explosion]
[MINISTER] (aaahhh!)
[WAVE] He did it!
[general panic]
[TATSUMI] (waaahhh!)
(slight gasp)
I'm sorry.
I guess I broke my promise.
(sobbing)
You gave me your word!
Tatsumi... Tatsumi...
Is it over?
Has the empire... fallen?
Have we failed Our reign?
Tatsumi...
is dead.