[BOLS]
Is this the bandit fort
we've been looking for?
[DR. STYLISH]
Uh‐huh!
Our first mission as Jaegers
is to tear this
unsightly place apart.
[RUN]
How shall we go about it?
Justice should always be direct.
Strike from the front!
Hm...
Hmm...
[TATSUMI]
So uh, why'd you
bring me here?
[TATSUMI]
You're part of the
Jaeger reserves.
I suggest you watch and
learn for future reference.
[TATSUMI]
Uh! That's the bitch
who killed Sheele!
I can't lose my head right now.
Remember what Bro said...
it takes more than passion
to survive.
I have to get back to base.
I have to get back and
report everything!
Oh...
This could be...
the perfect chance to get away.
Uh...
Mmm...
Oh shit, not anymore!
[Clanging]
[BANDIT]
You're pretty stupid to
attack us head‐on.
Koro! Phase 5!
[Bark]
[Roar]
Hehe...
Kill them!
[SERYU]
Judgement of the Ten Kings!
Devil King's Justice Lance!
Next!
Phase 7!
Cannon of Justice!
[DR. STYLISH]
Hehehe. All those weapons
are my fabulous designs.
The Hands of God, "Perfector",
stylishly increases the
wearer's dexterity
hundreds of times over!
Oooh, I am just living
for this Imperial Arms!
[Screams]
After all the fighting,
I'll get to play with
your body parts.
Like precious little dolls.
Ahh!
Uh?
[WAVE]
You don't have to thank me
for saving your ass.
We're a team y'know.
No. I knew he was there.
Oh yeah, right.
[Screaming]
[BOLS]
The flamethrower Imperial Arms,
"Invitation to
Purgatory Rubicante."
Nothing personal guys, okay?
[Gasp]
[BANDIT]
An angel...
[RUN]
Wing‐type Imperial Arms,
"Soaring for Miles, Mastema."
I cannot allow a single one
of you to live.
Hmm...
[TATSUMI]
Whoa...
Tatsumi.
‐Hm?
‐Soon you'll be able
to do that too.
I'm going to train you.
[TATSUMI]
That's awfully
generous of you.
I'm not like all
the rumors say I am.
To be honest, I haven't
been quite myself lately.
I've started to
experience love.
And well, it feels good.
Hm...
[TATSUMI]
Maybe this means...
I might be able to convince
her to join OUR side.
Yeah!
I mean...
I could never forgive her for
everything she's done,
but if she could change her ways
and help us overthrow
the Empire...!
[Gulp]
Okay, I'll win her
over tonight!
Come on, Tatsumi,
turn on that manly charm.
[Tatsumi's heart
beating faster]
Things got hot and heavy
a little quicker than
I thought!
[Ding]
Uh! Snap out of it, man!!
Okay. Don't freak out.
Just convince her to join
the revolution!
Do it. Take control!
Take her down like a tomcat!
[Meow]
I must not let her
intimidate me!
[Gulp]
Sorry for the wait.
No, no it didn't take
that long at all!
Can I get you a drink?
Uh, no, no!
I think I'm fine.
Hm? You seem a bit nervous.
Huh? No!
What, I'm not nervous!
Mm... Aren't you just adorable?
Well, I don't know very much
about these feelings either.
It'll all work out if we just
let our bodies take over.
Uh... So, I uh...
I wanted to ask you.
Miss Esdeath.
You like me don't you?
‐Uh!
‐Mmm.
If I didn't, then I wouldn't
be in this bed with you.
Um... in that case,
could you just hear me out
real quick?
Hm? Of course,
what's on your mind?
To be intimate we must
know each other.
It's just, the Empire's
kind of a mess right now.
I imagine a lot of citizens
would agree with you about that.
What's your point?
If I'm gonna be doing
this kind of work,
I think maybe I should be
part of the Revolutionary Army.
And I'd really like it if you
and I could join them together.
Just think of all the lives
we could save that way!
Tatsumi.
[Slap]
Uh...
You do realize that you're
speaking to a General
in the Imperial Army.
I know this may sound
completely ridiculous to you,
but unless things change,
we could end up having
to fight each other!
Uh!
There's no need for you
to worry about that.
I'll be keeping you
by my side forever.
I know you're unsatisfied
with the life you once knew.
But with me you'll never
need to want for anything.
And I promise
I shall be faithful.
I won't even look
at another man.
You'll never feel
alone again.
Oh...
It's not that I don't
appreciate the sentiment,
but I can't.
It's not right if I'm the
only one who finds happiness.
So you have a family then?
I can offer them
full protection too.
‐That's not it.
‐Uh!
Listen, I want to live
in a nation where
everyone can enjoy
their ordinary lives.
So, that's why this messed‐up
Empire needs to be torn down.
Tatsumi.
Don't you understand?
Of course not!
I feel no empathy
for the fragile.
[ESDEATH]
"The strong feast upon
the flesh of the weak."
That's the law of the land!
Those who die, are not
strong enough to survive.
No. There's no way I could
fall in love with anyone
who thinks that way!
If you care about me even a
little bit, then please!
You have to learn
to love life!
[ESDEATH]
That face... I love it...
Tatsumi, that'll never happen.
Understand something.
You're never going
to change who I am.
You will be the one
changing for me!
That's all there is to it!
You can't expect me
to change what I believe
just because you tell me to!
Even if you torture me!
Hm, you're so headstrong.
Perhaps that's why he was
able to smile so freely.
I must have his heart.
I must have Tatsumi as my own!
Well, I'm sure you must
be tired after today.
We'll discuss it more tomorrow.
For now we should
get some sleep.
Ehh...
Okay, I'll be over here
on the sofa.
You can sleep in
the bed tonight;
I won't do anything to you!
Oh yeah!
Then I should probably
take a shower!
[ESDEATH]
Just so you know.
If you wander around the palace
or make any attempt to leave,
you will be executed.
Please do not try
anything foolish.
Don't worry about me...
That's true,
the guys warned me about
how dangerous the palace is.
Ah. I should've had us
shower together.
Well, no reason to rush things.
[ESDEATH]
Therefore, not only is he
a part of our reserves;
Tatsumi here is also
going to be my lover.
Now, if any of you are married
or in a relationship,
please raise your hand.
‐Whaaa?!
‐Don't tell me YOU
have a girlfriend!
[BOLS]
A lovely wife of six years,
actually!
She's such a wonderful woman;
I really don't deserve her!
Then maybe you can help me.
What can I do to encourage
Tatsumi to return my affections?
Ooh, the trick is to
never giving up!
I'll tell you a secret.
My dear wife turned me
down twice
before I found the
perfect moment
and swept her off her feet!
So bear in mind that
it may take some time.
But it will be worth it.
That's very helpful.
Well, I can certainly
be determined.
You WILL fall for me
in the end, Tatsumi.
It'll be a fun little game.
[WAVE]
Hm?
Hey! How did you
sleep last ni‐
Oh wow, you didn't sleep at all.
No, I was so nervous I stayed
awake until the sun came up.
She said she wouldn't
do anything,
but when I woke up
she was spooning me!
You sure do start snacking
early in the day, Kurome.
Mind your own business.
You should try to
eat more seafood,
it's really good for you.
I wouldn't want to smell
like fish all the time
like you do.
What? Really?
Do I smell like fish?
Oh, uh, no not really,
yeah you kinda do.
Hm?
Something about the way
that girl looks...
and her name Kurome,
she just seems
familiar somehow.
Uh!
‐Keep your eyes
off of my cookies!
‐Ah...
And she's so protective
of her food!
Yep, she must be
related to Akame!
Gotta problem?
Oh, uh... Please don't
be offended,
but you really look like
that Akame girl from
the wanted posters.
Right! I noticed
that earlier too!
Well yeah. I'm related to
that goody‐two‐shoes.
[KUROME]
But now she's a traitor
to the Empire.
I do hope I run into
her again soon.
You know why?
So I can be reunited
with my dear sister...
And kill her with my bare hands.
Uh.
Tatsumi! We're off
to Fake Mount.
We'll spend the next
few days hunting.
Where's Fake‐Mount?
You've never been there?
It's in the range beyond the
outskirts of the Capital.
[TATSUMI]
We're going to the country!
I can finally escape!
[ESDEATH]
You two will be joining us.
We're hunting Danger Beasts
as well as bandits.
[BOTH]
Roger that.
Kurome and I will take
the east throughout the day.
Wave and Tatsumi, you're
in charge of the west.
We'll exchange
partners at night.
So Tatsumi will
be with me.
‐Eh?
[ESDEATH]
The monsters that come out at
night are especially vicious.
It'll be my chance
to impress him!
[Tatsumi groans]
[WAVE]
I didn't want to say this
in front of the team,
but you've got it pretty
rough, don't you?
Let me know if you
ever need to vent.
Uh, thanks a lot.
But I'll be okay;
I mean, I was already
used to being treated
like that anyway.
Yeah. Trust me,
I understand that.
I just get this
weird feeling
you and I are kinda
similar, don't you?
Similar? What do the
two of us have in common?
Huh? Uh... I'm not sure
how to explain it.
It's like we deal with
the same problems...
or at least GONNA deal
with the same problems.
Uh yeah.
I totally get it.
We're practically like brothers,
You and I are exactly the same.
Well, let's work together!
We can share each other's
pain and‐ Uh?
Tatsumi?
Uh..
Gah!
Look out!
[Roar]
[WAVE]
Whoa! Thanks for that!
[TATSUMI]
No big deal.
I just saved his life without
even thinking about it.
But, I should probably get
outta here while I still can!
[WAVE]
They keep popping up
outta nowhere!
And they don't look edible
like the ones on the coast.
You ready? Let's wipe
these suckers out!
[Both grunt]
Phew... That wasn't
so bad was it?
You finished over
there, Tatsumi?
Uh... Tatsumi?
Wha...
Where'd he go?
[Running footsteps]
[TATSUMI]
Imperial Arms users
probably don't expect
people to get away from them.
But since I have one too, that
doesn't really apply to me.
Tatsumi?
Where are you?
Ah! Did he make a
break for it?!
Nooooo!
Dammit, dammit, DAMMIT!
I know how you must feel,
but I can't let you get away!
I'm too young to die!
I guess it's time.
Grand Chariot!
[Roar]
[TATSUMI]
Maybe this is far enough.
He wouldn't chase me
all the way out here, right?
Uh!
Wha... what was that?!
It's an armor type.
Just like mine!
[WAVE]
Well, how about that?
I can't believe what I'm
seeing right now.
That's Incursio, isn't it?
It's the prototype for MY armor!
And most importantly...
If you have Incursio,
that must mean you're
a member of the Night Raid!
[TATSUMI]
Oh!
[WAVE]
Time for a change of plans!
Killing a member of Night Raid
is way more important
than finding Tatsumi.
[Tatsumi grunts]
[WAVE]
And though my model is newer.
And supposed to have
better stats.
I should be cautious anyway.
[TATSUMI]
Is that Wave in there?
Or someone else?
Either way...
I'm screwed if
Esdeath shows up!
I gotta get outta here!
Uh!
[WAVE]
You're not getting away.
Now man up and fight!
[TATSUMI]
Stop it!
I don't have a reason
to fight you!
[WAVE]
Yeah maybe you don't...
but I sure as hell have
a reason to fight you.
You're Night Raid trash!
[Tatsumi coughing]
[Wave]
I read the file on you guys.
You assassinate people
at random.
You threaten the safety of
the Imperial Capital.
And worst of all, you're working
with the Revolutionary Army!
Criminals like you
shouldn't be allowed to live.
[Grunt]
[TATSUMI]
Shut up.
It may be true that
we're assassins.
But I am not...
WE are not...
[Dragon roars behind him]
We are not the bad guys here!
[WAVE]
What's he doing?
[BULAT]
Takes more than passion
to stay alive, you know!
[TATSUMI]
Oh...
That's right.
No matter what, I have to
make it back to the base
so I can tell everyone
what I learned!
[WAVE]
If you're not gonna
come after me,
I'll just have to
force the action!
[TATSUMI]
Crap!
[WAVE]
Grand Fall!
That was a solid hit!
I'll have to keep track of him.
I can't let him use
the water to escape.
Wait, where'd he go?
Aw, crap...
He could be using the
current to slip away.
Nice try, but that'll never
work on a man of the sea!
Ugh... I didn't have to
fight him after all.
I guess Grand Chariot
can't go invisible.
Uhh...
[Coughing]
Damn.
That last kick was
pretty brutal.
Good thing I focused on defense
or that would have killed me.
At least now I think
I can finally go home.
[Birds flying off]
Huh?
[Beast growling]
Woah!
A Danger Beast?!
Shit! Why did you have to
show up right now?!
Ugh! This isn't good...
I'm too weak to fight
after all that.
[Roar]
This is it!
Uh!
A‐Akame?!
Tatsumi.
Are you okay?
How did you find me?
We were doing everything we
could to keep an eye on you.
Wow, you guys really did that?
All that trouble just for me?
Sorry, guess you ended up
saving me again, huh?
[Thud]
Ow!
I'll always be there
to save you.
Because you're my friend.
Hm...
Akame...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just relieved
to see your face.
Hm...
Welcome back, Tatsumi.
Yeah.
Good to be back.
[LUBBOCK]
Whooo!
‐[TATSUMI] What are you doing?
‐[LUBBOCK] Haha!
C'mon, we don't have
time for sweet talk!
Hurry up, we're going this way!
[TATSUMI]
Thanks for your help
back there, Lubb.
Yeah, no sweat.
It was kinda my fault
for bringing up that
stupid tournament.
If anything happened
to you, then I'd be
the only guy left!
Well, maybe that'd be okay,
I'd have my own harem!
Man, you're hopeless.
Don't you listen to him;
he was worried sick
about you the whole time.
[TATSUMI]
Yeah, I know.
Night Raid...
when I'm with these guys...
it really does feel like home.
[WAVE]
Uh, I don't know
what else to say.
Except I'm very sorry for
what happened, okay?!
General Esdeath, I humbly beg
your forgiveness!
Tatsumi got away because
you weren't paying attention.
What I cannot overlook,
is that a member of Night Raid
slipped through your fingers.
Kurome, more weight!
M‐hm.
Ahhh!
Oh my dear Wave.
Your technique is impeccable
but it's worthless if you
don't use your head.
Please try to correct this.
[WAVE]
Okay...
Oh and next time
you disappoint me...
I will be delivering
your punishment myself.
Is that perfectly clear?
Yes, ma'am.
Commander!
Deepest apologies!
Koro hasn't been able to
track him down yet!
[ESDEATH]
Hekatonkeiru is
built for combat.
Don't let it upset you.
Where's Dr. Stylish?
[SERYU]
We still haven't
heard from him.
Well, I'm sure he's
found nothing.
[RUN]
Commander.
May I ask a
question concerning
the young man
you're interested in?
If he did turn out
to be an enemy,
then how would you
like us to proceed?
[ESDEATH]
Honestly, I still care
for Tatsumi very much.
The harder something is to get,
the more desirable it becomes.
However, the lives of my
subordinates are more valuable.
I'd prefer if you took him
alive, but I'm giving you
permission to kill him.
[Run]
As you wish, Commander.
Tatsumi's been
infected with evil,
so we should just
vanquish him right away!
[ESDEATH]
Tatsumi, if they actually
manage to kill you,
you aren't much of a man.
But you're stronger than
that, aren't you?
You're powerful. A survivor.
I feel it, Tatsumi.
I can't help but believe
our paths might cross again.
No, I'll make sure of it.
And when they do,
I'll force you to accept
my feelings for you.
I'm coming for you, my love.
[TATSUMI]
And that's everything
I found out
about the Jaegers
and their weapons.
Gahhh!
So all of those guys
can use Imperial Arms?
Man, this blows.
I still can't believe
Kurome's one of them.
But when you left the Empire,
why didn't you bring
your sister too?
[AKAME]
I asked her to come with me.
But she decided to stay behind.
So from Kurome's perspective,
I'm just another traitor
who ran from the Empire.
[TATSUMI]
I bet when Zanku showed
her that illusion,
it was of Kurome.
[MINE]
Well. Now that you've seen those
jerks up close and personal,
what's your opinion?
If we're talking
one‐on‐one,
I don't think any of the
Jaegers are tougher
than we are.
It's just...
Esdeath.
I've never seen
anything like her.
As of now, I really don't think
I stand a chance against her.
Esdeath may have amazing power.
But she still has a weakness.
[LEONE]
And what's that?
[AKAME]
She's alive.
Her heart is beating
as we speak.
Therefore,
I can still kill her.
I don't care if she's
the strongest, most
evil person on Earth!
[Dr. Stylish laughing]
Aw, how precious that they
tried to cover their scent
and hide their footprints!
But since I brought my
super‐enhanced soldiers,
it won't do any good.
Hehe... I knew there was
something trés funky
about that boy.
You wouldn't expect a blacksmith
to adjust that quickly,
am I right?
[Snap]
Bingo!
Peekaboo, Night Raid,
I see you.
[Music playing]