[Woman crying]
Please! Don't kill me!
[ZANKU]
No can do, sweetie,
this is what you two get
for being out at this hour.
Didn't your parents
ever teach you
that dangerous men roam
the streets at night? Hm?
Please let me go.
I'll do anything you want!
Is that so?
Well, I'm a bit of a talker.
Will you have a little chat
with me?
Yes! I will! I'll talk!
Great!
Then tell me, how does it feel
to be without a body?
What's wrong, feeling torn?
Mmm, simply delightful!
The perfect end
to a perfect day!
[Grunting]
[Panting]
That's enough for me, Bro.
My arms really hurt.
Hm?
Come on! You've still got
some excess movement
in those muscles of yours.
[Straining]
Just concentrate.
You have to sharpen up
your focus.
If you can cut out all that
extra movement
you'll be able to hang in
there twice as long.
I got it...
You'll be an unstoppable force
before you know it.
You just need a firm touch.
Oh... OH!
[AKAME]
Tatsumi.
It's time for you to
help me make breakfast.
Ah!
Hm...
[Chopping food]
What are we making?
It's croquettes and rice.
Croquettes and rice
for breakfast?
She really is a psychopath.
Whooo!
That hit the spot!
Ah gawd.
My poor stomach.
Hold on.
Are Mine and Sheele
still in bed?
[AKAME]
Yeah. They always
sleep this late.
[Clears throat]
I just witnessed the speed
of a true assassin. No doubt.
Tatsumi.
We'll be serving tuna
and rice for lunch.
Akame, behind you...
[SHEELE]
Hm? What happened to
my breakfast?
[An eagle screeches]
[NAJENDA]
You did well.
What about the others?
I think I'm the only one who
was able to make it this far.
I see.
This is a list of everyone
in power
who swears to help us
when we rally.
It's in my hands now.
You can rest easy.
Please, help the revolution...
Right. I promise.
Your next target is the
serial killer everyone's
been talking about.
He appears at night
and decapitates people
seemingly at random.
Right now, the number of
victims is unknown.
I'm pretty sure a third of
the people he killed
were guards...
must be strong.
No doubt about it;
definitely sounds like
Headhunter Zanku's work.
Huh? Who's Zanku?
You don't know?!
Wow, you really are from
the sticks, aren't you?
Sorry, but I don't think
I've ever heard of him either.
[MINE]
Seriously, you probably
just forgot, Sheele.
Ahh...
Okay, so what's so terrible
about this guy anyway?
It's worse than you can imagine.
Headhunter Zanku used to be
the executioner
at the biggest prison
in the Empire.
The Minister orders a lot
of decapitations.
Over and over,
day in and day out.
And one by one,
Zanku chopped off their heads
as they begged for their lives.
Over the years it became
an addiction...
and now he can't stop.
[TATSUMI]
That's enough to drive
anyone crazy.
Uh‐huh. And eventually killing
prisoners wasn't enough anymore,
so he took it to the streets.
Zanku disappeared shortly after
a subjugation force
was organized to catch him.
I never thought he would
turn up in the city.
Then what are we waiting for.
Let's take this bastard out!
Whoa, easy, tiger!
Yeah, but‐
Zanku's also equipped with
an Imperial Arms
he stole from the warden
a few years ago.
We'd better travel in
teams of two...
in case it's a rough ride.
Jeez, why did he have to
say it like THAT?
By the way...
do we have any idea
which Imperial Arms
he might be fighting with?
No, we're still looking
into that.
Not about to reveal his
hand then, is he?
That's annoying.
So uh... what IS an
Imperial Arms anyway?
Ah!
Something like this.
That's... not that helpful.
Very well then.
Why don't we get Tatsumi
up to speed?
A thousand years ago,
the Emperor who built the Great
Empire was deeply troubled.
[Emperor]
I wish I could defend this
nation until the end of time,
but someday I will die.
However, weaponry and armor
can last generation
after generation.
We will combine our wisdom and
create weapons to protect
my empire forever!
[NAJENDA]
He gathered materials from
S‐Class Danger Beasts
and rare metals such
as Orichalcum.
Artisans from around the world
were summoned to help him.
The Emperor's wealth and power
allowed him to forge 48 weapons‐
a feat that would be
impossible today.
He called them the
"Imperial Arms."
Each one is equipped with
amazing abilities,
and some are able to
wipe out entire armies.
Ministers who used the
Imperial Arms
were quite successful
on the battlefield.
But a large civil war
500 years ago
caused nearly half of the
weapons to be scattered
across the land.
And that's how it all began.
[TATSUMI]
Is Akame's sword really
one of those 48 weapons?
[NAJENDA]
The One‐Hit Killer: Murasame.
When someone is cut
by this sword,
a poisonous curse enters
the body and kills
within seconds.
There is no antidote.
Hundred‐Beast King
Transformation Lionel.
This belt gives the wearer all
the strength and swiftness
of a wild animal.
It also enhances the
sense of smell,
making it perfect for recon.
The Adventurous Bunker, Pumpkin.
A gun that fires mental energy
in the form of a shockwave.
The more danger its
wielder is in,
the more deadly it becomes.
The Demon Armor, Incursio.
A suit of armor with
impregnable defense.
Wearing it causes such
great strain
that any normal person who
attempts to put it on will die.
The Protean Cross‐Tail.
A string‐based Imperial Arms
that can be used to set
traps and barriers,
as well as attack
enemies directly.
It's just as versatile and
dangerous as the name suggests.
The Shears of Creation, Extase.
A giant pair of scissors sharp
enough to cut anything in half.
They are also strong enough
to be used defensively.
Some Imperial Arms also
have trump cards.
Incursio maximizes the abilities
of the beast used to create it,
allowing its user to become
temporarily invisible.
Most importantly...
the Imperial Arms have followed
one iron‐clad rule from
time immemorial.
These weapons are so incredible
that whenever two of them clash,
it always ends in death.
Therefore, if two Imperial
Arms users choose to fight...
one of them will
definitely perish.
We know Zanku has
an Imperial Arms.
While mutual death is a
possibility, mutual survival
is clearly not.
Okay, I see...
Uh‐oh! Looks like we've
revealed way too much to
let you outta here now.
So unless you wanna die,
I guess you're just
stuck with us for life.
Uh... yeah!
That's a good thing, Tatsumi.
It means that the Boss considers
you a part of the team now.
While it's true that Night Raid
is lacking in numbers
we make up for it with our
individual abilities.
I believe we're the
heart of the revolution.
What about me?
Do I get one?
What?! You really think we have
a weapon we can just give you?
Huh? You don't?
Haha... If the
opportunity arises,
I'm sure you'll be getting
your own soon enough.
Hm...
Nothing further at this time.
Now let's go punish this
scumbag. Move out!
Roger that!
This is the area we're
supposed to be checking out.
All the locals are
so terrified of Zanku
that they're staying inside.
But he could still get‐
‐Keep an eye out for guards.
‐Hm‐hm...
Hey, Akame, can I ask
you something?
Not to worry.
I made sure to bring
enough food for both of us.
Oh... no, not that.
Is it true that your sword
kills with one strike?
That's right.
Oh, man... it's a miracle
I'm even alive right now.
I've been using Murasame for
a very long time...
and over the past few years
it's built a reputation as
the "One‐Hit Kill Sword".
Shouldn't that be a secret?
Well I guess it's invincible
either way though, huh?
No. It still has some drawbacks.
Some drawbacks?
It's almost impossible to clean.
If I cut my finger, I'm dead.
I must cut directly into my
opponent's flesh
or the curse won't
get into the body.
It must be tough if the enemy's
got thick armor. Like Bro does.
For me everything depends
on one‐hit‐kills.
That's why I can't afford to
rely on just my Imperial Arms.
Akame is probably somewhere
near the same age as me...
but I have to wonder
how many battles she's
already had to fight?
Hmm!
Now we have some assassins
and a serial killer running
loose in the Capital.
My, what a jungle
this city can be!
How exciting!
Good evening, Night Raid!
I wonder, which head should
I go after first?
Ooh, look at the sense of
purpose in those eyes!
I'm impressed.
I know what I'll do!
I'll go after the tastiest
morsels first.
It's not like he's just
gonna waltz right up to us.
Guess all we can really do
is be patient.
Uh...
I'll be right back.
Is nature calling?
[Tatsumi sighs]
I must be nervous.
Huh?
Sayo!
Hey! Where're ya going?!
What's taking so long?
[Panting]
I can't believe it.
It's really you!
I‐I thought you were dead.
Thank God, you're okay.
Oh how touching!
Uh?
I must've shown you
something very nice.
Oh?
Good evening, my friend.
Wh‐what the hell did you
do with Sayo?!
I would prefer you to call me
a different name...
and please say it with love.
My name is Headhunter Zanku.
So you're the one.
I've been looking for you.
"Uh‐oh! Looks like he managed to
separate me from the others!"
"Maybe I'll be able to
stall him for a minute!"
Is that what you're thinking?
Did he just read my mind?!
That must be his Imperial Arms.
Bingo!
You're right,
it's called Spectator.
And one of its five special
gifts is known as "Insight."
It allows me to read
your every thought
by gazing at your
facial expressions.
Obviously, it's blessed me with
keen powers of observation.
Should I give you a shiny gold
star for guessing correctly?
Don't bother!
And you can stop
talking any time now!
Oh no, I love a good chit‐chat.
Do you want to know how I
managed to find you?
No matter how dark or
how foggy it is,
my "Far‐Sight" can see
clearly for miles!
Delightful!
Did you think you could
land a hit
if you attacked me
mid‐monologue?
Only one problem.
I'm still reading your mind
like an open book;
have you forgotten that?
[Roar]
First you're gonna come right
at me with a downward slash!
Then you're going to try
your finishing move!
Then try to fake me out and
go straight for my throat!
Heh! You really are
so predictable.
[Gasp]
He's on a different level
than anyone else I've faced!
I love the look on people's
faces when I remove
their heads...
it never ceases to give me
such a rush!
[Grunt]
The thing that gets me most.
Is how they always look
so surprised.
I wonder what kind of delightful
expression you'll make?
You're not gonna live
long enough to find out!
Huh?
Tatsumi...
[Screaming]
Ooh, I do appreciate ambitious
young people like you!
In fact, I think you're gonna be
a perfect new addition
to my collection of
shrunken heads!
[Crazy laughter]
Just delightful!
I must say I've really done
a number on that firm
resolve of yours.
Agh... what?
That pitiful sound of a
"tough guy" like you
begging for mercy is
music to my ears.
That's why I'm compelled
to take my time.
[Grunt]
Yes! Please feel free to beg!
Maybe you can buy enough time
for your little friend to
catch up with you, eh?!
[Spit]
Don't hold your breath.
You're just some filthy bastard
who gets his kicks
from chopping off heads.
There's no way in hell
I'm begging you for anything!
If he can read my mind, I'll
have to keep things simple.
I'll try one more attack...
and give it everything
I've got!
Oh... aren't you courageous?
And you're in so much pain too!
It's a good thing you're in the
hands of an expert executioner.
This is it!
Huh?
Ugh!
Ah!
Uh! That little shit.
He's quicker than
I anticipated.
Ha! It's about time
I got one in.
Ugh!
An expert executioner, huh?
An expert wouldn't have
missed my neck!
Some Headhunter
you turned out to be!
Shut your mouth!
He looks pretty upset.
You must've used some of your
own psychological tactics.
Akame!
Glad I got here in time.
Just sit tight while I
finish him off
and then I'll tend to those
wounds of yours.
Hehe...
Well if it isn't Akame and
her infamous Murasame.
How delightful!
Nice to meet you, dear.
It's so nice to
meet you as well.
Since you're my target.
X‐Ray!
Hmm... she's not concealing
any weapons.
Ugh... Be careful, Akame!
That eyeball thing can
read your mind!
I see.
I wondered which Imperial Arms
he'd be using. No matter.
It makes no difference whether
he can read my mind,
if he can't keep up!
He's good. He's seen
his share of combat.
She's not just fast,
she's powerful too!
[Grunts]
Wow, so this is what combat
between two Imperial Arms
users is like.
If he can read my mind,
we're evenly matched.
In that case...
Well done, you've
cleared your mind!
But Spectator has
"Foresight" as well.
I already know what your
next move will be...
Exactly!
Uh!
Ah!
[Crazy laugh]
He actually put a
scratch on her!
Come on, now!
It wouldn't be very fair
if I didn't get to
rough you up a little bit,
now would it?
You can see what I'm thinking
and what I'm about to do.
I'd say we're even.
So, Akame.
Tell me, how do you deal
with the voices?
Huh? Voices?
[Haunting whispers]
Listen! When it's quiet
you can hear them.
The people I've killed are
screaming at me from Hell.
They sound so angry
and they're constantly telling
me to hurry and join them
down there!
I've been hearing them every day
since I became an executioner
and it keeps getting worse!
I just keep talking
to drown out the noise.
So tell me what you
do about the‐
I don't hear them.
Your voices.
I don't hear anything like that.
Interesting.
You're such an
experienced assassin,
I thought for sure
you'd understand.
You have disappointed me!
[Gasp]
Kurome.
[TATSUMI]
What's wrong, Akame?
Hey, snap out of it!
She can't. "Illusionary Sight"
creates a mirage
of the person you care
most about in this world.
Right now she's looking at
a vision of someone
so important to her she can't
bring herself to do harm to me.
Huh? So that's why
I thought I saw Sayo!
Akame please!
Don't let him get to you!
It's not real!
Don't bother!
It may only work on one target
but it's extremely hypnotic.
Besides, no matter how much
skill you have...
Nobody can make themselves
kill the one they love
the most, can they?!
This is the last thing you'll
see before you die, Akame...
enjoy it!
What the...?!
She didn't even hesitate!
What the hell?!
You were supposed to see the
one person you love the most!
My desire to kill her.
Is because I love her so dearly.
[Panicking]
What is she saying?
Now it's time for
this battle to end.
[Gasping]
No, it's about to break!
I'll destroy that weapon first!
[Screams]
I refuse to die!
Reading her mind gives me
the upper hand!
No, I can't kill her
quick enough!
My sword won't
last that long!
Ah!
Gah!
Ugh!
You are done.
[Gasps]
You did it!
Akame. She saved me ...
I need to get stronger.
Zanku...
those voices will never
haunt you again.
The voices...
they're gone.
It's delightful...
I thank you...
Akame.
Sayo.
What are you doing?
It's time for dinner.
You may be injured but you can
still pull your weight.
Hey, Akame?
Who was it you saw when you
were hypnotized by Zanku?
Hm?
I'll tell you when
the time comes.
I will tell you this much:
Everyone in Night Raid.
They're all important to me.
That includes you too.
Gah!
Let's go.
Uh, hey, wait up!
It's all meat dishes tonight.
No way; that can't be healthy!
Can't you throw in a few
vegetables here and there?
‐Nope.
‐Come on!
[Music playing]