[LUBBOCK] (snoring softly)
[LEONE] (groaning)
[LEONE] Oh God...
We may have celebrated
a little too hard last night
for Tatsumi's return.
[TATSUMI] (snoring)
[LEONE]
Guess we all crashed out here.
[LEONE] (yawns)
Sleepy, sleepy...
(hmm?)
[TRAUMA] (evil giggle)
I've done it, Master Stylish!
Your trusty assistant Trauma
has done iiiit!
Good work, now let's
continue the mission.
He got the first one,
Doctor Stylish.
[STYLISH] Marvelous! That's my
little knight in shining armor,
flying straight into
enemy headquarters.
All right...
Go, Beautiful Team Stylish!
[TEAM] Hyah!
The Dapper Offensive is
officially underway!
[EYES]
The soldiers have made their way
into Night Raid's base.
[STYLISH]
Ah, let the show begin!
I'm tingling with anticipation!
[LUBBOCK]
(heavy breathing) Holy crap!
Where'd they come from
all of a sudden?!
They're already on top of us!
(gasps)
How the hell did they
even get in?
[STYLISH GUY] The enemy...
must be killed.
(swoosh)
(whipping sounds)
(ungh!)
This is bad. I need to find
the rest of the team, NOW!
(stretching sounds)
[STYLISH GUY] (nggghhh...)
[LUBBOCK] (gasps)
[LUBBOCK] (UNGH!)
It sounds like they got one.
Well, my enhanced fighters ARE
more resilient than humans.
It takes SERIOUS finesse
to put even a scratch on them.
(gasps)
Is there some kind of problem?
Not really. But they seem
pretty resilient themselves.
[LUBBOCK] You'd be amazed how
many awesome tricks I can do
with this little bit of string.
CHECK THIS OUT! Hyah!
KYAH!!!!
(swishing sounds)
[LUBBOCK] All I have to do is
bind them all together, and...
VOILA!
(UNGH!)
[STYLISH GUY] So creative...
Saw that in a manga one time.
You wouldn't believe it,
but those crazy things
are full of ideas of how
to manipulate string.
(gasps) Crap, another one.
[STYLISH GUYS] (grrr...)
Nope. More than one.
Ah, sorry I'm not
so good with groups.
I think I'm just gonna pass on
you guys, if that's cool.
(WAAAHHH!!!)
[STYLISH GUYS]
(continued growling)
(hysterical panting) (huh?)
Ah, dammit,
they're pretty fast!
Stay behind me Lubbock.
Yeah, I can do that!
[STYLISH GUYS] (growling)
(snick ‐ swish ‐ snack)
(low whistle) Nice one, Akame!
(approaching footsteps)
Wait!
[LUBBOCK] You want some too?!
[TOBY] Impressive for
a couple of thugs.
He's strong.
You can call me Toby.
And I'm here to battle you
one‐on‐one, Akame!
(schnick)
(swish) (grinding whir)
(clang)
This one's different.
I felt it when I attacked.
His entire body is mechanical!
Akame!
(small explosion)
[LUBBOCK] (gasps)
Giants, huh?
OKAY!
(large explosion)
(hunh) (urk) (ungh) (gyah)
[ALL] (ungh!)
[KAKU]
Hey, you in the tin can!
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
[KAKU]
Nice of you to show yourself.
Seems you're the fella
I'm s'posed to kill,
so let's get down to it!
[TATSUMI] (gasps)
Those scissors!
(chuckles) Oh, these?
The Shears of Creation Extase.
Just picked these up.
[TATSUMI] Give those back.
THEY DON'T BELONG TO YOU!
(hyah!)
(swink) (snap!)
[TATSUMI] (gasps)
[KAKU] These babies'll cut
anything! (chuckles)
[TATSUMI] (gyaaahhh...)
Pretty good reflexes boy.
I was gonna take
your whole arm off!
[TATSUMI] (ungh)
[KAKU] (laughs)
No matter how thick
that armor is,
I can cut right through it.
So, how's it feel to know your
armor is useless against me?
Your little outfit
won't do you any good!
Sounds like we have the upper
hand over Murasame AND Incursio.
Exactly how I planned it.
It's easy to defeat somebody you
have a strong aversion to.
But still, we've already lost
quite a few soldiers.
There's too much noise
in the area for me to
determine the exact number,
but the death count
is extremely high.
Oh dear, what a tragedy.
(chuckles) Just kidding!
Those silly pawns are
WONDERFULLY dispensable.
They're just criminals anyway.
Poor dolts are always happy
to cut a deal with me
if they think it'll
shorten their sentence!
Little do they know,
they're nothing but fancy
fodder waiting to die!
[TATSUMI]
Those belong to Sheele!
Give 'em to me NOW!
Huh? Who the hell is Shell?
[TATSUMI] (ungh!)
[KAKU] (laughs)
You must really feel
like dying today.
How about I start cuttin'
some stuff off?
[TATSUMI] (unhhh...)
[MINE] Real brave,
picking on a pipsqueak.
Huh?
You're even more pathetic
than I thought.
[TATSUMI] Mine!
[MINE] (gasps)
So those pieces of crap
couldn't handle you by yourself,
and now it's my job?!
[MINE]
I'm ready to get this over with.
Seeing Extase in your big,
ugly hands is starting to
piss me off.
So you wanna get this over with?
Be careful what you ask for,
cause you're gonna get it,
sweetie!
In case you haven't noticed,
we took over your base!
You've been made,
and it's all but done!
That's why I'll make it quick.
(YAH!) Do you know who
you're talking to?!
(umph)
Stupid little girl!
She knows I was able to
withstand Incursio's attacks!
What's she gonna do with
that pea‐shooter?
(powering up whine)
(gasps)
(gunshot)
[KAKU] (waaahhh) Nooooo...
(clang)
[MINE]
The more intense my fight,
the more intense my weapon.
You should not have
underestimated me.
(crying)
[MINE]
You're coming home, Sheele.
(ungh)
Kaku has been defeated.
And they've almost finished off
the whole infantry.
(sarcastically)
Oh my goodness gracious,
what a tragic turn of events.
I'm afraid that does it.
Time for Plan B.
(gasps)
Doctor, there's something
flying over us.
Huh?
(wind rustling)
(gasps)
That must be
Danger Beast Air Manta!
And someone's riding
on its back.
Wait a second...
It's ex‐General Najenda!
Looks like she's got two other
people with her, too.
[STYLISH]
Oooh, delightfully dramatic!
Valiantly riding on a
Danger Beast she tamed herself?!
[NOSE] Now don't get yourself
all worked up!
[NAJENDA] Headquarters was proud
of their fortune‐telling Arms.
It predicted trouble
near the hideout,
and it came to pass.
Glad I flew back
as soon as I found out.
This is your shot, recruits.
Time to show me
what you're made of!
(heh)
Well, isn't THIS a fun surprise?
It actually works out
great for me.
Every one of you
is going to become
a test subject for
my experiments!
It's time to unveil
my trump card!
[clang!]
(grrr!)
If I can't finish you
in a single hit,
then I'll have to
chop you into pieces.
And it's gonna hurt.
You better get ready.
(hmph!)
That's where you're mistaken.
Given my condition,
I can't feel pain anymore!
Hyah!
Yah!
(gunshot)
(shwack)
[TOBY] (ungh)
(grrr!)
(gunshot)
[TOBY] (UNGH!)
(grrr...)
Damn you!
This wasn't even your fight!
My home and all of my friends
are in danger.
Do you honestly expect me
to just sit back and watch?
[TOBY] Well... As it was going,
I would have lost
that battle anyway,
even if he hadn't interfered.
Akame... please tell me...
Why was it impossible for me
to win against you?
Your fighting style was
extremely aggressive,
but you left me
too many openings.
Obviously.
[TOBY] (chuckles)
I should've focused
more on defense. Right?
A sense of pain is quite the
useful luxury after all.
(SHWACK!)
[TATSUMI] What is that?
More enemies?
[MINE] Hang on, I'll check.
Whaddya know?! It's the boss!
[TATSUMI] Sweet, perfect timing!
Wait, that's not fair!
[MINE] What's not fair?
[TATSUMI] How come they get
to ride on a giant fish?!
I wanna ride a fish!
[MINE] Umm... I'm not sure
I know exactly how to
respond to that.
(giggling)
Oh, you adorable little lady!
YOU SEEM TO HAVE LEFT YOURSELF
WIDE OPEN! (chuckles)
[TRAUMA] (GNUGH!)
[LEONE] You really caught me
off‐guard didn't you?
[TRAUMA] (gaaahhh)
I was passed out and hung over
and you throw a knife at me?
That is grounds for a serious
ass‐kicking my friend!
[BOTH] (uhhh...)
[TRAUMA] (choking) Put me down!
I can't breathe!
Word of advice.
I'm a huge fan
of surprise attacks,
but if there's one thing
I hate about them,
it's when they happen to me!
Your body looks like
it's been enhanced,
but I wouldn't expect that to
make your death come any easier!
(choking)
(shwing)
[TRAMA] A‐ha!
(gasps) Well, she's just full
of surprises isn't she?
[TRAMA] (ungh)
Ow... He did manage to get in a
good one, and man does it hurt!
Oops! Oh crap!
I think I killed him.
[TATSUMI] Um... Sis?
[LEONE] (hmm?)
[TATSUMI]
You're okay now, right?
Yeah, he just surprised me
at first, that's all.
But I can regenerate pretty fast
when I'm in my beast form,
so I'll be just fine!
Everybody okay?
[TATSUMI] Yeah!
[MINE]
Good, I think we're all here.
(swoosh)
[AKAME] (huh?)
[TATSUMI] Looks like we've
still got some work to do.
This doesn't make sense.
How did they get in without
setting off my traps?!
I'm not picking up anyone else's
smell either.
[TATSUMI]
Whatever, we're all together
so let's just knock these
losers out, okay?
Right!
[AKAME] (gasps)
[TATSUMI] (huh?) Akame!
Wha...
what's wrong with you guys?!
[MINE]
I can't... move my body... argh!
[TATSUMI]
This sensation... it's just
like what happened on that boat!
Hypnosis, maybe?
[AKAME] No... I think...
it's... it's....
Seems to be working perfectly
on all targets
except the one
wearing Incursio.
[STYLISH] (laughs) That's the
effect of my trump card.
A fast‐acting paralysis agent I
made all by my stylish self.
Aaah! But won't our allies
be poisoned too?!
Obviously, the good
doctor remembered
to treat them with
the antidote, moron.
Oooh, Master Stylish,
you're like a super genius!
[STYLISH]
It's not like I intended to
try out my latest concoction
on such promising subjects,
you know?
See? It's a very
valuable creation
and I went to great
lengths to make it!
But I had no other option!
They were wiping out my lovely
cohorts so quickly! (sobbing)
We understand, Master!
You're so kind!
Yes, and the poison has no
smell, so it's easy on my nose!
[AKAME] (ngggh)
[LEONE] (ungh)
[TATSUMI] I'm holding up better
than anyone else right now.
So it's all up to me!
(explosion)
[ALL] (unhhh)
[TATSUMI] (uhhh...)
Is he... with us?
[NAJENDA] Now! Exterminate every
foe you see, Susanoo!
Understood.
(swoosh ‐ snick ‐ whir)
[ALL] (ungh!)
Yahhhh! (oofff)
(gyah)
[TATSUMI] What... the...
Sir! One of them has jumped down
and is now pulverizing
the entire infantry!
But that's impossible,
the poison should affect
every living being in the area!
Maybe not. He might have an
unlisted Imperial Arms.
In which case,
I guess I don't really need
to include him in my research.
Oops!
(explosion)
[ALL] (ungh)
[STYLISH] (laughing) Do you like
my deluxe human explosive?!
Ha! One down!
[ALL] (heavy breathing)
[TATSUMI] (gasps)
Oh my god... don't tell me...
I've only heard of these.
He's an organic.
He's a human Imperial Arms!
(hmm?!)
Um... what are you...
Fixed.
[MINE] Wait, what?
[ALL] (huh?)
Whoever did this found a spot
where he could easily spy
on everyone.
He's probably hiding
somewhere upwind
so the poison
can't get to him.
If there's somebody calling
the shots from above...
then he must be
somewhere over...
There!
Susanoo! They're on the cliff
to the southeast!
Don't let them get away!
[SUSANOO] Understood.
[ALL] (gasps)
[EARS]
We've been discovered sir!
Nothing to be done, is there?
All we can do now is RUN!
[ALL] (wha?)
Poison doesn't affect
organic types!
You must either destroy the
core or immobilize the wielder!
[ALL] (waaahhh!)
My, my, she's even more
tenacious than I thought!
There's nothing to be afraid of,
Master Stylish!
[NOSE] We are your guardians
until the bitter end!
I promise you're in good hands!
[STYLISH] Oh, please,
you don't stand a chance.
I designed you three for recon,
not hand‐to‐hand combat.
Now that it's come to this...
(grrr...)
I'll have to protect myself!
And play my second trump card,
Danger Beast Shot!
Sorry, but you
leave me no choice!
[EYES] You okay, Master Stylish?
What's wrong?
[STYLISH] (unngghhh...)
[NOSE] Sir?
Oh, what an impeccable
sensation!
This is the ultimate
in nouveau riche!
I've successfully merged my body
with a Danger Beast,
so I may personally
kick your ass!
[NOSE] He is GORGEOUS!
[EYES] Very impressive, Master!
[BOTH] (huh?!)
But first I'm going to need a
little sustenance, yes?
(yum...)
Time for us to become ONE!
[EYES & EARS] (screaming)
[EARS] (panicked breathing)
(screams)
Just as I expected, scarfing
down all this nutritious meat
is helping me level up!
[TATSUMI] What is that thing?!
He's a mutation.
(BOOM!)
[MINE]
And he's totally gross!
[STYLISH] Well this isn't bad,
but I'd still like to be
a scoche bigger.
That Imperial Arms guy got me
pressed even when I'm a giant!
I suppose if I truly desire
to win this battle,
I'll have to grow even larger!
Prepare yourself,
to be devoured alive!
[SUSANOO] (nnggghh)
Interesting.
[TATSUMI]
Oh crap, I'd better go help him!
[AKAME] Wait! Tatsumi...
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
I can't walk, but I need you to
take me with you, okay?
[TATSUMI] Akame?
Sure!
You might wanna hold on tight.
Now, let's do this!
(laughing) Where are you going,
Mr. Fancy Pants?
Are you too afraid to attack me?
(BOOM ‐ BOOM)
(huh?)
[SUSANOO] (hmph)
And you two!
Playing some piggyback?
I'm sorry.
But that's just tacky!!
(BOOM)
(unhhh)
[STYLISH] You're wasting
your time, darling!
The One‐Hit Killer Murasame
won't do much good
if it can't pierce my skin!
Now, perhaps it's time
to give up! (ungh)
[STYLISH] Damn you!
(gunshot)
[TATSUMI] You've lost all
your little pawns.
You do know its almost over,
don't you?!
(panicked breathing)
I'm not done yet!
[TATSUMI] I bet you can reach
his flesh from here!
Go for it, Akame!
(shwack!)
[AKAME] You're done.
No... there were still
so many people
on which I wanted to
experiment...
I...I never thought it would
end for me this way.
I pictured more panache.
(ba‐dmp!)
(THUD!)
[BOTH] (slight chuckles)
You were lucky to die with
all your parts intact.
Don't take something like that
for granted.