[WAVE] I don't get it. I feel
like we've looked everywhere.
Where could their hideout be?!
[SUZUKA] Well, Kyoroku is
an extremely large city.
And since this religious
organization is a fairly
peaceful one,
we can't do anything drastic
to lure them out.
It's going to take more than
simply attacking someone.
[children laughing]
Here!
[KORO] Woof! Woof!
Kids are so cute!
They're still so young and pure,
they haven't been
tainted with evil!
[SUZUKA]
Wow, I never realized she could
actually smile like that.
Yeah, she'd been stressed
for quite a while.
So Esdeath told her she should
try a little change of pace.
By the way, you've been
hanging around a lot lately.
Have you decided
to join us or what?
Hmm... I guess we're "partners."
Whatever it takes to get General
Esdeath to put me in my place.
(slightly crazed giggle)
[WAVE] I'm not sure why,
but something about this girl
reminds me of Dr. Stylish.
See ya! Remember to have fun
playing and never cheat.
Okay, boys and girls?
Wooofff!
[CHILDREN] Okay!
[SERYU] It's so nice to
guide them down the path
of righteousness
while they're young and
impressionable!
Yes, this is what is right.
This is my country!
I'll protect it at all costs.
[AKAME] That's all the info
the spies gathered.
We will launch the plan
the day of the
Path of Peace celebration.
Wow, going out with a bang, huh!
During the festival,
we'll slip through the crowds
and sneak into the palace.
Then we'll go in for the kill!
[thwack]
[TATSUMI] Serves him right.
This job will send the
Revolutionary Army into action!
Failure is not an option!
[ALL] (uh‐huh)
[SUSANOO] Dinnertime, everyone.
I pulled out
all the stops today.
Is everyone ready to have
their minds blown?!
[ALL] Yeah!
[SUSANOO] Najenda gets ramen.
The noodles are extra firm
and the balance of chicken
and salt is just right!
[NAJENDA] Ooh!
[SUSANOO]
Mine gets strawberry parfait.
I even added a little
something extra.
[MINE] Yummy!
[SUSANOO] And for Lubbuck, I've
prepared a fresh Bohai shrimp.
[LUBBOCK] Ohoho!
[SUSANOO] Leone gets oden and
assorted local brands of sake!
[LEONE] Yeah!
[SUSANOO] For Akame,
I have a collection of meats
from every beast I could
find in the forest.
[AKAME] Ahh!
[SUSANOO] And Tatsumi said he's
not picky so he gets,
well... this.
[TATSUMI] Huh?
But this looks like it's
for little kids!
[MINE] (snickers)
As a special treat,
I had Susanoo cook up
everyone's favorite food.
So go ahead and chow down;
you're going to need energy.
[ALL] (slurping & gobbling)
Oh, no need to tell you twice.
I'm glad everyone's hungry.
Mmm! So sweet! I love it!
Tatsumi, you gotta
try a bite of this.
Tatsumi, you do know what
you're s'posed to do
when my cup starts getting
empty, don't 'cha?
Yeah, yeah, okay,
I'll pour you some more.
Hee hee, that's right;
you're such a good boy!
[TATSUMI] (choking gurgles)
[AKAME]
(gulping) (contented sigh)
Good God! You ate all that?!
[AKAME] Another amazing meal.
Thank you, Su!
[TATSUMI]
Yeah! Seriously, I don't know
what we'd do without you.
You're awesome!
I'm deeply honored to know
I've pleased you.
But, Tatsumi...
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
[SUSANOO] You didn't eat
the last grain of rice.
I don't know if I can stand it.
Sure is a shame.
This guy would be perfect
if he wasn't such
a ninny all the time.
[SUZUKA] If Night Raid plans to
strike, it'll be today.
But that goes without saying,
doesn't it, Seryu?
Suzuka, do not let those demons
into the cathedral, okay?
Yeah, I know. (oh?)
[SUZUKA] That girl's got
combat experience.
I can tell by those eyes
and the way she walks.
[running steps]
[TATSUMI] Damn! Didn't take 'em
very long to spot us.
[MINE] They won't chase us
all the way out here.
[TATSUMI] Yeah, well,
we had to get out of the city.
I hope we created a good
enough distraction.
[MINE] All we can do now
is cross our fingers
and pray the boss and
everyone else pulls through.
It feels like I still have
makeup all over me. Ugh...
Did I get all of it off?
(uh!)
Y‐yeah... yeah, I think so!
Why are you getting all red?
(urk) You're not taking all that
"string‐of‐fate" crap seriously,
are you?!
Oh, you wish! But it sounds like
YOU'VE been thinking about it
since you're bringing it up!
[MINE] Ugh, shut up!
Don't be ridiculous!
If you're my "soulmate",
then explain why you
didn't try to save me
when I almost got eaten
by that giant frog thing!
Where were ya on that one?!
[TATSUMI] Hey now, I kinda had
my hands full, remember?!
There's that Night Raid girl
I fought before.
So why in God's name is Tatsumi
with her? What in the hell?
(grrr)
He's been corrupted by evil.
Koro, Phase 9!
[KORO] (deep roar)
Justice City Detector!
There aren't any civilians
in the area.
(crazed giggle)
At last, destiny has reunited us
once again, Night Raid!
Koro and I will erase your kind,
with the swinging
Hammer of Justice!
Koro!
[KORO] (deep growl)
I'll give them a taste of my
explosive weapon
that combines Judgement of the
Ten Kings 2, 7, and 8!
The great commander
showered you with affection
and you repay her
with betrayal.
And now, you return with the
girl whose partner
hacked off my arms
and tried to kill me!
You shall be punished by fire
for your sins!
(ah!) I smell gunpowder!
Justice...
VOLLEY!!
[explosions]
(huh?) They survived that?
Stubborn little devils!
[TATSUMI] They certainly
seem to be after us.
Right? If you ask me,
they're trying to keep us
as far away from the town
as possible.
Must've struck a nerve.
Here comes another round!
Get ready!
[explosions]
[TATSUMI]
The attacks have slowed down,
so I guess we're out of range.
I got a look at the shooter.
It's definitely
Seryu Ubiquitous.
(huh?)
Seryu Ubiquitous, huh?
Which way is that bitch
shooting from?
It's the fourth Rakshasa Demon!
Suzuka.
But I don't suppose it makes
much difference what you call me
since you're about to be dead.
[TATSUMI] Oh, really now!
(hungh!)
Get outta here, Mine!
I don't think so!
After what she said,
there's no way I could just‐
Ah! Tatsumi!
[TATSUMI]
There's been a change of plans.
You get to fight me instead!
Oh, aren't you brave?
All right, I'll let you be
the first to die.
How does that sound?
[TATSUMI] (hyahh!)
Tatsumi!
Stupid.
Okay, you take care of her...
And I'll deal with Seryu.
After I finish my business with
her, I'll come back to help you.
[SERYU] Koro, Phase 6!
[KORO] Woorf! (deep growl)
What's that?!
Does she EVER run out of stuff?!
[SERYU] The rebellion will
never find peace!
Those with no value for justice
will meet their end!
[MINE] (short laugh)
Thanks for the big target.
[gunshot]
[big explosion]
[SERYU] What?! She took down
my most powerful attack
with a single shot! Fine!
Koro, Phase 1!
[KORO] Woof! (deep roar)
[gunshot]
[KORO] Woof! (deep growl)
(pained whimper)
[SERYU]
I came here to personally ensure
the condemnation of Night Raid.
[MINE]
So, we finally meet again.
[SERYU]
Koro's gonna eat your corpse,
just like he did
your two friends.
TWO friends?
[SERYU] (crazed laugh)
We put a woman's head on display
in the middle of Romaly,
a redhead I do believe.
And Koro ate the rest of her!
The same with that purple
freak in the glasses.
They both ended up in
a little pile on the back lawn.
And now it's your turn!
[MINE] You know,
you like to consider yourself
a fighter for justice,
but you blindly followed
Ogre and Stylish.
You never even stopped to think
about how messed up they were,
did you?
[SERYU] (grrr)
[MINE]
But then again, so are you.
You laugh exactly how those two
sick freaks used to laugh.
You're just like them.
That's why I have absolutely no
problem taking your life.
I'm gonna put
a hole through you!
Do you feel better getting
all that off your chest?
Koro, Phase 5.
[KORO] (deep growl)
Don't forget the arms.
[KORO] (deep roar)
All you managed to do was give
Koro enough time to regenerate.
The evil of this world
are so stupid.
Let's go, Koro!
[rapid gunshots]
[KORO] (roars in pain)
How is it so powerful?!
Maybe because
I've been holding back.
This fight'll be more
entertaining if it's
a true two‐on‐one!
The best thing about Pumpkin is
it fires with more power
if I find myself
in a tight spot!
[SERYU] Don't give up, Koro!
She can't possibly keep up
a surge like that forever!
Maybe not!
But thanks to our last battle,
I've almost figured out
where the core is!
I don't need much more time!
And then it's over.
[SERYU] Damn you!
Koro, use your trump card!
(huh?!)
(loud roar)
[MINE] I'm prepared for this.
I've seen everything this
Imperial Arms can do!
[SERYU]
Devil King's Justice Lance!
(gasps)
(short scream)
[repeated gunshots]
[MINE] She's more dangerous now.
Her personal weapon's not
an Imperial Arms,
but it's really strong!
[rapid gunshots]
[SERYU] (ungh)
[SERYU] (furious scream)
[gunshots]
I'LL BEAT YOU TO DEATH!
(arrrgghhh!!!)
(ungh!)
(panting)
I took on too much damage.
Shit, I should've just
finished her off.
[MINE] (un...ghhh...)
(giggles)
[TATSUMI] This girl is
really freakin' fast.
She's all over the place.
(giggles)
Aw, you made me break a nail.
[TATSUMI] Son of a...
[SUZUKA]
Killing Mez, that was one thing,
but I was surprised
one of you took out Ibara.
Though it clearly
couldn't have been you.
It's painfully obvious
how little combat experience
you have.
[TATSUMI] Once again,
I'm not strong enough.
I've dealt with this regret
too many times.
Over and over and over!
No matter how tough she is,
I cannot let it happen again.
(ungh...)
(labored breathing)
[KORO] (deep roar)
Are you back at
a hundred percent now, Koro?
Good. It's time to destroy
this demon once and for all.
[general commotion]
(hyahh!)
Natara! Doya!
[LEONE] Oh, hey Su!
How are things going?
So far, so good.
We just need to stick to the
plan and lure the enemy here.
You must understand,
I don't have time
to play around with you!
Now where's my big sister?
Oh, you wanna know?
Okay, but before I tell you,
you're gonna pay for
cutting off my arm! (hyah!)
(ungh)
I'm still not healed
from the last fight.
Say your prayers, kid!
[WAVE] Stop picking on HER...
...and fight me.
Sorry I'm late, Kurome.
What? Do you want Su to send
your ass flying again?
Come and get me, Night Raid.
I'm not gonna let you hurt
my teammates anymore!
Grand Chariot!
General Esdeath, I need the
Jaegers; where are they?!
Shut up. You're getting just
what you deserve, Bolic.
If you'd listened,
you wouldn't be in this mess.
[BOLIC] You must protect me!
The minister himself commanded
you to‐ (urk)
[ESDEATH] You're right,
orders are orders.
I will continue to
keep you safe.
However, I must forbid you
to leave this room.
Yes! Of course!
[SUZUKA]
If your plan was to lose me
in the ruins, it won't work.
You'll just tire yourself out
and make your death too easy.
[TATSUMI] Yeah? Well sorry,
but you're going down
one way or another!
[SUZUKA] (wha?)
[TATSUMI] Get ready to join
your little friends!
What the hell?
This guy's gonna kill us both.
[TATSUMI]
You're not getting away!
This is your end!
(waaahhhh!)
This...
This brings back some memories.
How they called me a half‐breed
while they trampled me
in the street...
I just kept gazing into the sky.
No one ever stopped.
No one ever helped.
Then, I realized...
the only one
who could save me...
was me.
I made a promise to myself
that I would never live
such dark days ever again.
And I would never let anyone
else suffer such discrimination.
Which is why...
I will not die here
in the middle of nowhere!
(angry panting)
(hyah!)
[KORO] (deep growl)
Now!
I'll have my revenge!
[gunshot]
[SERYU] Koro!
The Ten Kings are
out of ammunition,
but I still have these!
[KORO] (deep roar)
Justice must prevail!
This is it!
(hyaaahhh!)
No! How could I let this happen?
My weapon creates power out
of emotional energy.
The more intense my feelings,
the more fuel for Pumpkin.
(unnggghhh)
[MINE] So the moment
you pissed me off...
that was when you lost.
[SERYU]
(increasing crazed laughter)
Justice will always prevail.
No matter what the cost,
all evil must be cast out.
[click]
[SERYU] Judgement of Ten Kings.
Final Phase:
Godotenrin's Furnace.
You've got one minute.
What the hell?! You bitch!
[SERYU] The doctor was kind
enough to give it to me,
the ultimate weapon against sin!
As long as it lives inside my
head, I can never truly lose!
Damn you!
Oh no, it's overheated!
(crazy giggle) (laughter)
You're too weak to get away!
You're not gonna make it!
You'll burn like
the demon you are!
(crazed laughter)
[KORO] (whining)
Koro...
You can't heal yourself anymore.
It's not fair; there's still so
much evil left in the world.
(crying)
I can't die until it's gone.
Not yet...
[KORO] (whimper)
(running)
Shit, my... my legs!
I cannot accept this.
If I die, how will I ever
fulfill my promise I
made to myself!
And I have to keep living for
the sake of Sheele and Chelsea!
Why would I suddenly
think of everyone?
I can't leave them alone;
they wouldn't have a clue
how to do anything without me.
(gasps)
[huge explosion]
Here it comes!
(ugh...)
[TATSUMI]
I was too weak when we lost Bro.
And I was too slow
when we lost Chelsea.
But that's it.
I will not lose anyone else.
(ah...) Tatsumi...
(chuckles)
Looks like you'll be okay.
(begins to cry)
[TATSUMI] Oh yeah, I did
exactly what you told me to do.
You said I should be there
to help out
whenever you're in trouble,
right?
[MINE] (huh?)
[TATSUMI] So that's what I did.
How about that?
Your bullcrap actually made
an impression on me.
[MINE] (huh?!)
Y'know, Tatsumi? You can be a
real patronizing asshole.
But...
I really do appreciate it.
Thanks a lot.
Uh... yeah, sure.
[ESDEATH] Bolic!
Where is that pig?
[NAJENDA] He already ran away.
Najenda...
[NAJENDA] It seems he
didn't take your advice.
I'm sure my subordinates are
silencing him as we speak.
[shnick]
(ugh) Nice try.
Horimaca!
But it barely even scratched me!
[swishing sounds]
[BOLIC] (chokes)
[ESDEATH] You always did come up
with clever little schemes.
Oh, yes. I like to think
I have a better understanding
of your talent than anyone.
So I wouldn't be so foolish as
to try to take you head‐on.
(tsch)
[MINE] I guess the fight's
over for now, huh?
[TATSUMI] Yeah.
[MINE] Hey, Tatsumi.
[TATSUMI] Hmm? What's up?
As soon as this is
all behind us,
I need to tell you something.
Can't you just tell me now?
No, I can't.
[TATSUMI] Wha... Why not?
I'm feeling so confused,
so conflicted.
I never imagined I'd want to
live for someone besides myself.
Promise me something.
Promise me you'll survive.
[TATSUMI]
Yeah, of course I will.
If these feelings
are driving me,
then I should be able to
tap into some powers
far beyond any
I ever have before.
From now on, my battles
will be even more intense.