Yes...
Perfect! It's all better!
It was nice taking it easy
waiting for my arm to heal,
but I'm ready to fight again!
With Sheele and Bulat gone,
I'll have to work extra hard!
Okay! Which one of you
is gonna train with me?!
(uggghhh)
Hey, Mine! What's up?
I'm glad your arm's
feeling better.
[MINE] What are you guys doing?
These pansies weren't getting
anywhere with their training,
so we decided to help out.
[TATSUMI] (straining)
I never realized...
until I actually put on
Incursio, how fast that thing
can take a toll on my stamina.
If I wanna wear it for
long battles like Bro did,
I'm gonna have to bulk up.
With the way I am right now,
I can only go invisible
for about a second.
It's a bit unusual to see YOU
getting all sweaty, Lubb.
Well since the team is down
to only two guys now,
figure it's about time
I started getting a
little bit more serious.
It's cute when you talk all big,
since you haven't done half as
many pushups as Tatsumi here.
[LUBBOCK] (grrr...)
But it's not his fault.
There's a considerable weight
difference between me and Leone.
(HUH?!)
(BANG!)
[AKAME] (awwwhhh)
[NAJENDA] Good, you're all here.
[ALL] (hm?) [LEONE] Boss!
[NAJENDA] I'm off to the
Revolutionaries' main base.
I'm thinking they'll need
the weapons we got from
the Three Beasts.
By yourself?
And you're taking that battle
axe? Isn't it kinda heavy?
[NAJENDA]
Nah, I can handle it. See?
Now there's no way I
could actually use it,
but I can at least
lug it around.
I had no idea
she was such a badass.
Of course she's a badass.
She used to be a general, man.
Akame,
I'm leaving you in charge.
I want everyone to buckle down
and train hard.
(ah!) Okay, whatever.
Hey! Could you be serious?!
Ah, don't worry too much,
Akame always gets the
job done either way.
(exhales)
I'm also going to the base
to try and recruit a couple
new members for the team.
Although, I highly doubt
they can afford to give us
anybody who's ready for
combat at the moment.
I'm sorry, guys. I'm trying
to get better, I promise.
(exhales) The Three Beasts you
defeated on the cruise ship...
They were at the center of the
Empire's offensive forces
and members of Esdeath's army.
But you and Bulat managed
to defeat them.
Esdeath may be a powerful foe,
but she's suffered a
devastating loss.
When the revolution begins,
we will have considerably less
to worry about.
You didn't just save passengers.
You ultimately saved thousands
of revolutionaries
who will be needed in our
struggle against the empire.
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
You are strong, Tatsumi.
And you're doing a great job.
(choked up) Yes, ma'am.
I didn't tell you before,
because I didn't want it
to go to your head.
But Bulat told me something.
Tatsumi's still got
a lot to figure out,
but I can see he has
amazing potential.
If we do a good job training
him, maybe he could even
improve enough to surpass me
one of these days.
I can't wait to see
what he does.
Thanks, man!
[NAJENDA] Take pride in
yourself, and survive.
That's all you can do.
Try your best to become
the kind of person Bulat
wanted you to be.
(trying not to cry)
[NAJENDA] Our need for more
members is critical.
Leone's report that Esdeath
is forming a special unit
entirely of Imperial Arms
users is disconcerting.
I have to do something.
Liver, Nyau, Daidara...
All three of you were killed.
I suppose that means
you were just too weak.
You've fallen victim to the
laws of natural selection.
Such incompetence.
I cannot change the past,
but I promise I shall
avenge your death.
The replacements will be
arriving today.
The word is they're a
smattering of eccentrics.
(hmph)
Might as well have some fun.
My name's Wave.
I served in the Imperial Navy.
I'm a man of the sea.
I'm here because I got promoted
to the special police force!
It's my first day in the
capital, so I'm kinda nervous.
But not to worry! I'm wearing
this awesome cool outfit,
so I'll be in with the locals.
It was a huge hit back home.
Yeah!
I'm gonna fit in just fine.
[GIRL] He's stinky!
[WOMAN?] Totally!
Besides, Mom even gave me some
of our highest‐quality fish
to share with my new friends.
People'll be offended if ya got
nothin' to offer, hon!
But I dunno...
[LOCALS] What's with him?
Frickin' redneck.
I could be imagining things,
but I feel like everybody's
staring at me.
Maybe city people have
different rules of etiquette.
[WOMEN] Where'd he come from?
‐ Somewhere gross.
(small chuckle) Oh well!
If I can handle fighting pirates
and aquatic Danger Beasts,
then this is nothing!
There's no reason to
stir things up!
Okay! My future teammates are
waiting behind this door.
First impressions
are everything!
I have to show I mean business.
[OLD MAN]
Don't let 'em walk all over ya!
Let 'em know who's boss.
Greetings, friends! I'm here
from the Imperial Navy...?
(aaahhh...) I'm so sorry!
Oh God, that was probably the
interrogation room!
Man, I'm such an idiot.
(hmm?) You're kidding!
I'm gonna be working
with THAT GUY?!
Uh... hello again!
I should probably do my best
not to piss this guy off.
Oh, crap, what'd I do?!
(nervous groaning)
Why is that freak still
staring at me like that?!
Oh, no... Mom, please don't be
ashamed if I come back home!
(door opens)
(huh?)
(aaahhh!) It's a normal person!
[WAVE] Uh, hi!
[KUROME] (huh?)
Nice to meet you,
my name's Wa‐ Heeey!
Stay away from my cookies.
Nevermind! Not normal.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Damn, these guys are wack‐jobs!
Hello, comrades!
(huh?)
I'm Seryu Ubiquitous,
member of the Imperial Guard!
And my friend's name is Koro!
[WAVE] (happy chuckle)
[WAVE] She's probably not
that crazy, right?
Please come grace us with your
presence, Dr. Stylish!
[KORO] Woof!
[STYLISH] Ah, I LOVE a good
dramatic introduction.
The very definition
of "stylish".
You've captured
my masculine grace.
Oh great,
now there's THIS guy?!
Oh my, you're just
a little country boy!
You're just too
adorable by far?!
[WAVE] (huh?!)
I'll polish you up
in no time, cowboy.
So don't be shy.
I think he likes me...
[RUN] Good afternoon.
Oh, it would appear that
I'm the last one to arrive.
Huh? Oh yeah, nice to meet you.
My name's Wave.
Hello there. Call me Run,
the pleasure's all mine.
(gasps) YES! There IS a person
here who doesn't freak me out!
[RUN] (ummm...)
[BOLS] Uh... excuse me.
The tea is ready,
if anyone would like some.
S‐Sorry.
I would have said hello before,
but I'm a little bit... shy.
Y'know, bashful.
Sorry, I... I'm sorry.
[WAVE] (huh?)
[BOLS] Whoo, looks like I'm
the oldest one here.
I really need to get my act
together, don't I?
I‐I hope we all
get to be close friends.
Call me Bols, from the
Incendiary Squad. Please.
[WAVE] (nervous laugh) Didn't
peg him for the shy type.
The Incendiary Squad...
That's the stylish unit that
will incinerate anything,
even living people.
Explains his
interesting look...
but he is NOT my type.
(uh‐umm)
(door opens)
[ALL] (hmm?)
[WAVE] And who might you be?
[ESDEATH] What in the hell
are you all doing in here?!
What's your problem?
We were all invited to come and‐
(ooofff)
(unghhh)
[ESDEATH] You never know
who's an assassin.
Don't ever let your guard down.
[ESDEATH] This one has
good reaction speed.
(crazy chuckle)
(gasps)
(ughhh)
[ESDEATH] You can't attack from
behind when your bloodlust
is so easily sensed.
(swish ‐ swoosh)
[KUROME] Not going to hold back,
even if this is just a game.
[ESDEATH] Must be the
Imperial Arms Yat‐su‐fu‐sa.
Just as sharp as expected.
(gasps) General Esdeath!
(ugh) God...
(gasps) So... even the
superior officer's a nutcase!
(heh!)
[ESDEATH]
I hope you found that enjoyable.
I didn't want to bore anyone
with a formal meet n' greet.
Nah, I'm used to a
little rough‐housing.
Your advice was very helpful!
Thanks a lot!
[ESDEATH] Good.
After we visit the Emperor,
we'll have a little party.
Wha?!
We're gonna meet the Emperor?!
With all due respect,
aren't we taking things
a bit too quickly?
I prefer to get the more tedious
things over with first.
Oh, by the way, General...
Have you decided on a
super‐fierce name
for the squad yet?
Yes.
We are an independently
mobile team
charged with hunting down
an elusive gang of
vicious murderers.
Therefore...
I'd like us to be called...
the Jaegers.
[WAVE] I love the idea of all
of us eating together,
especially since the meal
is the seafood I brought
for everyone.
But why are we the only ones
who know how to cook?
[BOLS] Wave!
[WAVE] (hmmm?)
The spinach goes in last.
It'll wither if you
put it in too soon.
Uh, you're right. I'm sorry.
Anyway, I wanted to tell you...
It's a huge relief to find out
you're such a nice guy, Bols.
[BOLS] N‐No, I'm afraid I'm
not all that nice.
Wooof.... Woof!
[SERYU] Commander?
[ESDEATH] Yes?
[SERYU] When you're not working,
what sort of things
[KORO] Woof! Woof!
do you like to do
in your free time?
Torturing prisoners... Learning
new methods of torture...
But as of just recently...
I've found...
an interest in love.
[BOTH] Love?
(soft chuckle)
Anyway, I've heard reports that
we have an extra Imperial Arms.
Oh! Uh, yes!
It's a scissor‐type weapon that
I have reclaimed from evil!
But we have yet to find
anyone who can use it.
The minister will confiscate it
if we don't find a wielder.
Which would be a waste.
To make things interesting,
we'll turn our search
into a little game.
[LUBBOCK] Yo!
[TATSUMI] Hey!
Come on in!
After you.
[TATSUMI] Whoa...
This really is
like a secret base.
[LUBBOCK] Yup!
It's my pride and joy.
Come on, it's not like you
built the place yourself.
Hel‐looooo! Welcome to our
Imperial Secret Base!
[LUBBOCK] (chuckling)
You're not being very secretive!
[LUBBOCK] Well, the Imperial
Guard's put up wanted posters
of some of us all over the city.
But there are still a few of us
who can still be seen out there.
Yeah, and if that isn't
enough for ya,
the whole capital's
been going crazy.
Some kind of special police
force called the "Jaegers".
That's because Esdeath
is in charge of it.
She's a pretty big deal
in this town.
You don't wanna mess with her.
Is this Esdeath chick
really all that dangerous?
You have no idea.
Okay, maybe I should
tell you the story.
So, several years ago...
A southwestern tribe raised
the standard of revolt
against the cruelty
of the empire.
So the empire sent the
army to quiet them down.
The tribe only had 10,000 men
as opposed to the
Imperial Army's 120,000,
so it seemed like the
outcome would be clear.
But it turned out to be way more
complicated than that.
Since the Imperial soldiers
were so used to their
cush city life,
they weren't able to survive
in the harsh wilderness.
Plus, the tribesmen
would attack at night,
so that made it even more
difficult for them.
The Empire started to panic, so
they dispatched General Najenda
and General Esdeath,
who were already extremely
talented despite being so young.
[NAJENDA] You seem to be in
a bad mood, General Esdeath.
[ESDEATH] (scoff)
Can you blame me?
The minister ordered me to
use Imperial Arms to
exterminate the rebels.
I'd hoped to take my time
punishing the forces who wiped
out the Suppression Unit,
but he doesn't share
my interests.
It takes all the fun out of
the whole thing.
But what can you do?
[ESDEATH] No matter if it's
Danger Beasts, killer insects,
plagues or viruses...
Anything that gets in my way...
will freeze!
(uggghhh)
(gasps)
[NAJENDA]
Her power... it's incredible.
We'll take over the enemy base,
okay?
Man, I feel like a cannonball
when I charge like this!
Artillery... FIRE!
(volley of gunshots)
[TRIBESMEN] (screaming)
As soon as you slaughter them,
you can enjoy your reward!
Have your way with
this wretched city!
(gasps) (disgusted)
[ESDEATH]
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Your precious home
burning to the ground.
You bitch! Just finish me off!
I feel like being merciful.
I think I'll take pity on you.
I'll allow you and
your friends to go free.
Like hell you will!
If you don't just kill me,
I swear you're gonna wish
you'd never come to this‐
(ungghhh)
[ESDEATH] Listen well.
Such is the fate that
befalls those who are weak.
Don't like it?
Make yourself strong.
[NAJENDA] What do I do? There's
no way I could obey an order
to slaughter those people,
nor can I stand with those
so ready to do so!
Well, that's the story.
It's pretty sick how she drilled
hate into those people
before letting them go.
Hang on though, from the
empire's side,
seems like she was
instigating the rebellion.
Yep, that's exactly what
Esdeath was trying to do.
She wanted to stir up
another uprising.
That way she could get her kicks
on the battlefield forever.
She sounds like a lunatic!
(big sigh) That was a close one.
I made the right choice
when I didn't pick a fight
with her by myself.
I mean, you would have to murder
like millions of people
to get a reputation like hers.
The way you guys are talking
about her,
she must be a monster!
You can check her out for
yourself if you want.
She's sponsoring a
martial arts tournament.
There's a cash prize
for the winner.
So you could earn some money for
your village while you're at it.
(uh...)
[EMPEROR] Uh, Minister...
Why do you think General Esdeath
is so interested
in falling in love
all of a sudden?
Everyone begins
to have these feelings
once they reach a certain age.
(chomp)
General Esdeath was
born to fight.
She has cared for
nothing but war.
Now, she's awakening to
her carnal desires.
Interesting.
It would be wonderful to
locate a match for her.
She's an incredibly
prideful woman.
She won't waste any time on a
suitor who doesn't meet her
criteria.
[EMPEROR] But how will we
ever find a man like this?
[ESDEATH] Number One: Above all
else, he must have potential.
I'd like to personally train
him to become a general.
Number Two:
He must have composure
and be able to hunt
Danger Beasts.
Number Three: Like me, he must
have been raised
in the frontier rather
than the capital.
"Number Four: I want someone
younger so I can dominate him."
"Number Five: He must be someone
with a pure and innocent smile."
(heavy sigh)
The majority of people
won't even get past
condition number one!
[MINISTER] Yes, there aren't
many men with the potential
to become generals.
(large crowd cheering)
(ungh!)
(yah!)
(wah!)
(yawns)
What do you think of the
contenders, General?
They're nothing
but pathetic rabble
floundering through
a street fight.
I seriously doubt
we'll find anyone
who can wield an Imperial Arms.
(crowd roars)
Oh, it looks like
these two are finished.
And the victory
goes to Nobunaga!
That's how it goes!
This next bout is going
to be the final match.
[WAVE] To my left:
Kalbi the Butcher!
To my right:
Tatsumi the Blacksmith!
He picked an interesting
fake job.
Think he knows anything
about blacksmithing?
Well, he's not as good as me,
but I guess he's
decent with his hands.
I see one of them
is pretty young.
[KALBI] (chuckles)
Well, look at you, little fella!
Looks like that prize money
is as good as mine!
I trained at
Imperial Fist Temple.
I was second degree
when they kicked me out!
The big fella's not all talk.
He looks pretty strong.
He might've intimidated me a
few months ago,
but I'm a lot different now.
Compared to those Three Beasts
I fought before,
this guy is nothing!
[WAVE] You may begin!
[KALBI]
You will feel the full force
of my Explosive Iron Fists!
I can beat this guy
without Incursio!
[KALBI] Yah!
(huh?)
[TATSUMI] Hyah!
[KALBI] (ungh)
(grrr...) Yaaahhh!
(continued fighting)
[KALBI] (UNGH!)
[KALBI] (ARRGGH!)
(GRRR!)
(WAAAHHH!)
[TATSUMI] KYAH!
(huh?)
(stunned murmurs)
He might be small,
but he's rather talented.
Yes...
[WAVE] And there you have it!
Tatsumi wins!
(crowd goes wild)
(huh?)
Are all these people
cheering for ME?
This is awesome!
(aaahhh...)
[ESDEATH] He's the one.
[RUN] He's our
Imperial Arms candidate?
[ESDEATH] Oh, yes, that.
But that's not all.
Commander?
(urk!) She's coming into
the ring herself?!
Tatsumi? Is that right?
That's a lovely name.
Um, thank you.
[TATSUMI] So this is Esdeath.
The one everyone's
talking about.
If it weren't for her,
we wouldn't have lost Bro.
[ESDEATH]
You put on an impressive show.
Now, for your reward...
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
Oh, uh, thank you
very much, ma'am.
No matter how you get it,
money is still money.
And I have no problem
taking it.
[LEONE] (hmm?)
[TATSUMI] Huh?
Starting today,
you'll be mine and mine alone.
Uh, wait a sec‐ (urk)
Let's go somewhere
we can be alone.
Too many eyes around here.
[TATSUMI] Hey! Hold on, you
can't just‐
Be a good boy. Okay?
[TATSUMI] STOP IT!
What'd... she do to me?
We'll talk further in my room,
just the two of us.
[BOTH] (HUH?!)
[LUBBOCK]
WHAT THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?!
So Esdeath took Tatsumi
away with her?!
Has she figured out he's a
member of Night Raid yet?
I can't really say for sure.
It's probably a 50/50 chance.
The last thing we saw was
her trying to drag him
into the palace.
What should we do now, Akame?
Tatsumi...
I won't ever make you sad again,
Akame.
[AKAME] (unhhh...)
Please don't say something
stupid like we need
to save him.
That won't work.
The first thing we should do is
move our base further from town.
[LEONE] Good thinking.
We're too easy to spot here.
[LUBBOCK]
Okay, but what about Tatsumi?
I'm not trying to say you WOULD,
but...
No, I understand.
I won't go charging in
without a plan.
But Tatsumi is still a
member of our team!
Do whatever it takes!