[KUROME]
How fun...
a battle between Imperial Arms.
How many will die?
[Roar]
[AKAME]
The more puppets she has,
the slower her reaction time.
That works to my advantage.
Ha!
Haaa!
Huh?
Natara?
Please put him to rest, Kurome!
You grew up together!
How could you say that, Akame?
I want him to stay close
to me forever and ever,
he's my special friend.
And I would love to add
you to my collection.
'Cause that way... we could be
together like the old days.
Not on your life!
[KUROME]
Too bad.
[BOLS]
Magma Drive!
[AKAME]
His Imperial Arms
can do ranged attacks?!
[TATSUMI]
Don't take them on alone!
This isn't like you, Akame!
Oh!
I'm sorry.
[TATSUMI]
These guys don't seem like
they're gonna go down
without a fight, do they?
[KUROME]
Big Sister...
it's a shame you betrayed the
Empire and sided with them.
Desta Ghoul!
Crush them!
[MINE]
S‐Class Danger Beasts are
worse than I thought!
That's incredible!
[KUROME]
Hehehe...
Well, that changed
the landscape at least.
However...
Night Raid doesn't get their
reputation for nothing.
They did manage
to dodge the blast.
Looks like the fight's
already started.
Najenda... Rest assured.
I will do the best
I possibly can for you.
And when this mission is over,
I'll tell you how
I really feel.
If I wait any longer...
Su's gonna nab you first!
[SUSANOO]
Its power is true to its class.
[NAJENDA]
Got it!
Everyone, work together!
[SUSANOO]
You didn't issue
the proper command.
Huh?
This Desta Ghoul may indeed
be a formidable foe.
But I can handle it on my own.
Assign the rest of
the team elsewhere.
Ah...
That's my Imperial Arms for ya!
[MINE]
Aim for the puppeteer...
I'll get her this time!
Ah!
Huh?
A gunslinger?
This should be fun!
[Beast growling]
[TATSUMI]
Is this thing a Danger Beast?
I've never seen
this type before.
Agh!
[TATSUMI]
Another one?
[HENTER]
Foolish...
[TATSUMI]
If it weren't for my
armor I'd be dead!
What is this guy?!
[HENTER]
Failure...
[AKAME]
These flames are so quick.
I've had enough.
[BOLS]
It's not wise to
charge from the front.
Uh...
Aah!
[AKAME]
Murasame doesn't work
on dead targets!
Ugh!
Akame!
Huh?
Whoa!
Congratulations.
You've made me mad.
I can see right through you
and your cheap little tricks.
Hey!
Even in beast mode, my eyes
can't keep up with that thing!
It's not like it's
an Imperial Arms!
Dammit!
[KUROME]
Well, look at this,
a battle royale!
How exciting!
Kurome!
See? Don't I have just the
coolest friends ever?
Doya, the gunslinger,
used to be an assassin who
worked for the northern tribe.
You can still see that tiny
spark of confidence on her face.
Wall was a very
famous bodyguard,
but he was protecting my target,
so I killed him.
Apeman is one of
my favorites,
he's easy to use and
hits extremely hard.
Henter was one of the last
survivors of a savage tribe.
His clever moves made him
difficult to beat
so he's my prized possession.
Rokugo was an
Imperial general...
but he betrayed us and
tried to join the revolution,
so I had to kill him too.
Oh, and I found this Desta Ghoul
while it was hibernating.
Talk about lucky!
And...
Natara's been with me ever since
I was a little girl!
He does a great job
of protecting me
whenever Yatsufusa
is activated.
I actually have one more puppet,
but you'll have to
wait to see that one.
No way...
she hasn't even
brought out the full set?!
[Fluttering]
Huh?
Dammit!
Wait, what?!
[KUROME]
That won't work.
They're already dead.
You can stab them all you want
and they'll keep moving.
You'll have to defeat me first.
Ugh!
Okay, buddy, I'll admit it,
you're pretty tough.
But!
I've got your pattern down!
I'm not gonna let you
keep hitting me
with the same attacks
over and over!
[NAJENDA]
Don't let go of that
whip, Leone!
General Rokugo.
Since you're a former colleague,
I'll do my best to free you
from this curse
as quickly as possible.
Whoa! I can't remember the last
time I saw the Boss in action!
Alright then! Let's do this‐
Uh...
[Gasp]
[KUROME]
Hehehe...
Oh dear...
that's why you should never
take your eyes off me.
Whenever I see an opening,
I'm going to take it.
I'll make you pay for this...
little tramp!
You should know better
than to make assumptions.
You're not the only
opportunist in this battle.
Argh!
Oh wow that's impressive,
you can stop the bleeding
all by yourself!
You made a mistake messing
with me, little girl!
I'm gonna eat you alive!
Hehe...
Don't engage her, Leone!
Remember, she has a bodyguard.
You'd better support Akame
at least for the moment.
When you're finished,
we'll face Kurome together.
Let the two ex‐generals
duke it out.
Rokugo doesn't have
an Imperial Arms,
so I should be fine.
[LEONE]
Yes ma'am.
Don't go anywhere...
I'm coming back for you.
I'm starting to think
you'd be the perfect
addition to my collection.
I'm surprised we haven't
caught up to them by now.
I don't like it.
It does seem like something's
not right, doesn't it?
[ESDEATH]
Perhaps this is a decoy
and Kurome's group is
the real Night Raid.
[Horse neighing]
[Thugs laughing]
And now we're running into
a gang of mindless meatheads.
Hard to believe this
is a coincidence.
[Thug]
Guess we heard right, boys!
[Hooligan]
She did show up here!
[Punk]
In the flesh!
So that must mean
these evil thugs
are working with Night Raid.
[ESDEATH]
‐Seryu.
‐Huh...
‐Run.
‐Hmm...
Destroy most of them.
But maim two or three and
keep them alive for me.
I have a few questions.
I can't run straight
towards him...
but I can...
Uh...
[BOLS]
She's searching for a window
while staying in
constant motion.
Very well...
I'll give her what she wants!
[AKAME]
There it is!
Armor on his hands?
Did he plan to face Murasame?
[BOLS]
I can't believe her reflexes!
Akame...
may I ask you something?
Why did you join the
Revolutionary Army?
It would have been so nice
to have you with us.
I chose Night Raid..
because my heart told me
it was the right thing to do.
I simply decided to follow
the path in which I believe.
[BOLS]
I completely understand.
I do.
And I'm sorry...
I'm afraid it's still my job
to eradicate you...
regardless of your beliefs.
Oh I gotta get in on this!
That'll make it a two‐on‐two!
Leone!
Yeah, you don't have to
worry about me.
Let's just concentrate on
the mission for now.
[AKAME]
Be careful,
they're strong.
[LEONE]
Whatever!
Let's waste this guy
so we can get Kurome!
[NAJENDA]
Considering I'm about
half as strong as I was
before I got these wounds
from Esdeath...
I'm swifter than I expected!
He's learned a new trick.
Earth Shaker?!
Ah!
We've been fighting for so long,
I can stay ahead of
anything you've got.
Fire! Reel Assault!
How 'bout we go out and
get a drink, Naje?!
Eh!
Uh!
What the hell kind of
Imperial Arms is this?!
Hyaaa!
[Beast growling]
Hm...
This is difficult...
but I won't be defeated.
Well, it IS an S‐Class...
are you having
trouble with it?
It hits really hard..
but the main problem
is right there.
Hm?
[SUSANOO]
That little bump is
getting on my nerves.
It's disgusting how it
completely breaks up
the symmetry!
If it wasn't so distracting
I wouldn't have gotten hit.
You're joking.
I swear you really
need to get over this
obsessive compulsive thing.
Still, if someone doesn't
get to Kurome soon,
we're going to start
suffering casualties.
Susanoo! As your master,
I am giving you permission
to use your trump card!
Understood.
[Growl]
[Hiss]
[TATSUMI]
They're so in synch!
If only one of them would
hold off for just a second!
Ugh...
Gah!
[Hiss]
[HENTER]
T...
Tri...
Tribesman...?
Uh...
Uuuuh...
[CHELSEA]
It's just like Akame said.
Yatsufusa's corpses don't have
a will of their own.
They're nothing but puppets.
But a few traces of their quirks
and their deepest feelings
do remain intact.
Sorry, but I'm not actually
a member of your lost tribe.
Aaaaah!
[CHELSEA]
Nice one.
He shouldn't be such
a nuisance anymore.
[TATSUMI]
Thanks for the help,
Chelsea!
Welp! Guess I'll leave the
big gorilla guy to you!
See ya!
Huh?!
[CHELSEA]
I can't believe I took such a
big risk back there!
And after everything I said
about Sheele and Bulat
being failed assassins.
Maybe all their sentimental
junk is starting to
rub off on me.
Oh Tatsumi.
Hmph...It's all your fault.
[TATSUMI]
Now that it's just you,
I can see your tactics!
Playing with the dead like
they're a bunch of toys...
this Imperial Arms
makes me sick!
Now... rest in peace!
[Groaning]
[KUROME]
Hm...
The intervals between
my snack breaks
keep getting shorter
and shorter.
I wonder if Wave's okay.
He seems fairly sturdy...
I'm sure he's alive.
Uh‐oh.
Rokugo and Henter
stopped moving.
Apeman too?
Guess it's time.
Before sending in
my final corpse,
I should probably
set another trap.
[Grunting]
[WAVE]
That was a serious hit.
If Grand Chariot's sword
hadn't blocked it, I'd be dead.
I have to get back...
or Bols and Kurome
won't make it.
Despite what Kurome thinks
of herself, she can be
pretty helpless.
If I don't help her‐
Auu... Auugh!
Dammit...
that hit must've been even
worse than I thought...
I can't move...
[MINE]
So, you're a sharp shooter.
Too bad you're up against me.
They don't call me a badass
sniper genius for nothing!
Huh? Uh? Ah!
Ew what is this nasty thing?!
Oh! That was quick,
it's already eating someone.
This is my new recruit,
the Kaiser Frog.
Its stomach acid is capable of
dissolving anything it eats.
It's delightfully deadly.
[MINE]
No! Let me go!
Oh, Seryu told me
something funny.
She said Koro gobbled up
one of your friends.
Uh!
It's kind of fitting that you'd
suffer the exact same fate.
No! There is no way in hell...
I'm gonna die in
a place like this!
Ahh!
The end comes much too
easily, doesn't it?
Bye‐bye! Hehe...
Good boy...
Ready for the next one?
[TATSUMI]
Stop right there, Kurome!
And don't think for a second
I'll go easy on you
just because you're
Akame's little sister!
Well. You don't know
when to quit, do ya?
Careful.
Natara's power is ten times
more intense than Apeman's.
[SUSANOO]
Magatama Manifest!
[NAJENDA]
Susanoo's trump card
makes him a berserker.
The emblem on his chest absorbs
his master's life force.
And he releases that
energy in combat.
After Susanoo uses this
ability three times,
his master will die.
But the trade‐off is
its incredible strength!
Eight‐handed Mirror Shield!
[Roar]
Sacred Sword of the Heavens!
[Blades clashing]
[TATSUMI]
He's on par with me while
I'm wearing Incursio!
No... he's even better!
[KUROME]
Hehehe...
It's all running smoothly.
Oh?
What's wrong little guy?
[Gunshots]
She's fighting from the inside?
But how is she still alive
swimming in all that acid?
Uh?!
Aww, it's leaking...
Oh no, that defeats
the whole point.
Uh!
Huh?
[Mine grunting]
Okay, I'm about ready
to kill a bitch.
[TATSUMI]
Mine?
What are you doing in there?
[MINE]
Oh, just got through
a living hell;
you could've
helped me, you know!
And don't look at me
like that, pervert!
How can you even tell
where I'm looking?!
[NAJENDA]
That's enough arguing
for now, you two!
We've got a battle
to win, remember?
[MINE]
Boss!
[TATSUMI]
Huh, what happened?
Why does Su look so cool?!
You wondered
how many will die.
Right Kurome?
I think I have
the answer for you.
Oh you think so, huh?
I get it.
I'll just have to kill
every last one of you...
that way you can be my
precious puppets forever.
Let's take him out!
Right!
[BOLS]
Uh? Why would they jump?
They can't dodge up there!
Now!
Uh...
[AKAME]
If the bodyguard is eventually
going to be in our way...
then we can surprise everyone
by going after him first!
No!
[LEONE]
He's locked in on Akame,
and his bodyguard isn't
there to help him anymore!
He's mine!
Ugh!
Sneaky bastard!
Ah, crap!
AAAH!
[Metallic snap]
Uh?
Hehe... [spit]
Tastes like you're
about to lose.
Did you actually just bite off
a piece of my weapon?!
[BOLS]
Ah...
[LEONE]
What're you gonna do
with your Imperial Arms,
it's nothing but a
hunk of garbage now.
[BOLS]
She's right,
I can't use it anymore.
Alright then.
Eh?
Huh?
I'll dispose of it.
Wait! No don't!
[Click]
[Music playing]