(Narrator):
The Tohtsuki
Fine Dining Academy...
an institute of fine cuisine
that continually produces chefs
of worldwide renown.
Chief among its highlights
is its Fall Selection,
a contest for first‐years
of the high school division.
After an intense
preliminary round,
winners move forward to face off
in the main tournament.
Where the fates of eight
contestants will be played out
on the big stage.
(Megumi):
Okay!
Oh no! My petite knife!
Did I make sure to pack it?!
There it is!
What about
my timer?!
I know I packed
it somewhere!
Oh God,
where is it?!?!
They're just EXPLAINING
the competition today.
You don't need any
of your gear, yet.
(panicked scream)
Are you sure?!
Girl...You're never
gonna change?
Hey...Megumi!
(Soma):
The car's already
here for us.
Huh?
Time to go!
(Narrator):
These eight elite
contestants excel
in both personality
and technique.
Waging a fierce battle with
their eyes on the top spot...
they await for
the curtain to rise...
on the final battle
of the Fall Selection!
(Isshiki):
Hey there Soma, the results
of the draw are in.
You will be competing
in the first round of the
upcoming competition.
Your theme will
be the bento box.
Bento box? Like,
normal bento box?
That is up to you.
Be sure to get all of your
prep work done early.
You'll be in the
finals tomorrow.
This is
a surprise...
Guess this school
CAN be down to Earth.
(Soma):
I mean, a bento
box? Really?
Do you even know
what you're saying?
You just don't
get it, do you?
The bento was developed in Japan
and has its own unique culture.
(Erina):
By using only the choicest
seasonal ingredients...
the bento has remained beloved
in many culinary circles.
The word "bento" is now
even in the French dictionary.
It's an appropriate theme for
a celebration of haute cuisine.
(Erina):
If you even know
what that MEANS.
A sharp line divides it
from second‐rate drab cooking...
which happens to be
YOUR specialty.
(uncomfortable laugh)
Sure enough, that's one thing
I don't like about you.
(scoffs)
I'm good with listening
to people and getting them
to talk more
openly....
but you're just
too much, Erina.
Ugh!
Coming back from the
training camp
was pretty
uncomfortable, huh?
What do you mean?! What does
that have to do with ANYTHING?!
I swear to God,
Soma Yukihira! UGH!
Hm?
I swear to God,
Soma Yukihira! UGH!
This is unusual. Nakiri is
actually raising her voice.
Very well. I have a
client to attend to.
(Eizan):
If you'll excuse me.
Soma Yukihira.
Promise me you will give it
your all and win tomorrow.
(Eizan):
You don't want to lose
your first battle.
That would be
disappointing.
So...
who will I be
competing against?
(Urara):
The moment you've all
been waiting for is here!
It's the finals
of the Fall Selection!
Contestants ready?
Audience ready?
Let's begin the first battle
of the competition!
First up is the contestant from
A Block, tied for 2nd place,
Soma Yukihira!
Aww yeah!
Kick some
butt, Soma!
(Urara):
And the opponent
he will be up against...
the contestant who nabbed
the top spot at B Block...
Alice Nakiri!
(crowd cheering)
Alice Nakiri...
(Takumi):
This can't be good.
She's the granddaughter
of our school director.
she's competed in countless
competitions and won them all.
She's a genius known as the
Prodigy of Molecular Gastronomy.
Her curry dish had the best
score in the preliminaries,
and used the very latest
cooking techniques.
It definitely
made an impact.
How will you possibly
combat this, Soma?
(Alice):
Aren't you lucky?
Get ready to be
enthralled today...
by me and my cooking.
(Male Student 1):
Awesome!
(Male Student 2):
Look at her equipment! It's
like... from outer space!
(Zenji):
Sitting up here
in the stands,
has my sensitive skin
tingling with anxiety.
To think, he has to take
on the Nakiri family HERE.
Yeah. The
pressure is on.
He definitely has his work
cut out for him.
It really is a shame,
now, isn't it?
We're finally
together on stage...
and I'll only get to experience
your famous cooking once.
Yeah, but if you lose...
you'll see more sitting
up there in the stands.
Ah, yeah... I don't think
that's gonna happen.
(Alice):
Your skills rely
on mostly showmanship
and are hopelessly outdated.
They're no match for
a trained culinary mind.
(exaggerated yawn)
Well, look at you.
Too worried to get
any sleep last night?
Yeah... I was up pretty
late trying out ideas.
Before I knew it,
it was already dawn!
But you don't
gotta worry about me.
This battle is
pretty normal fare
for me to have
to contend with.
(Soma):
We've got guests
with picky tastes...
Knives sharpened
and gleaming...
and ingredients
all laid out.
The only thing different,
is havin' to go up against
a tough industry
rival like you.
Alice... I'm going
beat you today...
and add everything I've
learned to my repertoire.
Here we go, folks!
(Urara):
The theme is bento boxes!
Two hours will be
placed on the clock!
NOW, LET...
(Senzaemon):
the Cooking BEGIN!
(crowd cheering)
Good luck, Soma.
You can do this!
It's like some
science experiment.
Zenji, explain
all this!
I can't...
this cooking is outside
of my frame of reference.
WHAT ARE THOSE
NERD GLASSES FOR?!
(Alice):
Mmmm!
The Japanese DNA inside me
is quite happy with my
gastronomic prowess.
(Soma):
Ooooh!
Huh? What's wrong?
Well, you made fun of
showmanship earlier...
but you're pretty
good at it.
Well, of
course I am!
Jeez... you're
such a dolt!
And don't you know
it's not polite to stare?
It's funny, I remember getting
the full stare‐down from you
at our last
training camp...
(Male Student):
He's going up against the school
director's own granddaughter!
Dammit! Soma, please,
tell me you have at least
some kind of plan!
(Takumi):
Yes... I'm sure he does.
(Urara):
Now then...both contestants
are about to finish up.
Looks like the first
one done will be...
(Urara):
It's Alice Nakiri!
Well... who's
ready for lunch?
What is that contraption?!
Inside that dome it looks
like... there's smoke?
That's something I could
never even imagine.
Ah... she's put out
something strange again.
(Saotome):
How fitting for a
celebration of fine cuisine!
This presentation
piques one's interest.
(students in awe)
Temari‐zushi, eh?
Yes! I have showcased my
vast culinary techniques
into this specialized
temari bento box.
This is VERY exquisite!
(Senzaemon):
Hm. This "smoke" is
actually liquid nitrogen.
I see that your intent
was to preserve
the sushi's freshness
using cold air.
Gentlemen please...
if you wouldn't mind, I'd ask
that you eat this bento in order
(Alice):
from the top left.
First, we have the
bounty of the sea...
abalone topped with a
delicate touch of foam.
I made this portion...
by turning a stock of
kombu seaweed into foam.
(Alice):
And the toppings were pressed
between sheets of kombu.
(Hisako):
Sandwiching them in kombu,
removes a bit of moisture
and also preserves them.
It's a good cooking
technique for a bento box.
Yes, it is.
But I don't think that's the
only reason for using kombu.
(Alice):
This is skipjack tuna...
It was aged for two days
at low temperature,
bringing out
its bold flavor.
Mmm...MMM! How
exquisitely divine!
(slurp)
It's wonderful...
the umami's complex!
Note that the tuna
has inosinic acid
while the kombu
contains glutamic acid.
When combined, the umami
components create a lovely
synergistic effect.
(Alice):
By eating this bento
in successive order,
the umami profile grows more
complete on the refined palate.
(Male Student 1):
Oh, my gosh!
(Female Student):
I wanna eat that!
(Male Student 2):
That looks incredible!
(Alice):
Next... we come down
to the second row.
These are so‐called "cake sushi"
made using vegetables.
There is absolutely
no seaweed.
Vegetables sliced paper‐thin
were used to wrap
the ingredients.
After all, a variety of colors,
adds to the eating experience.
(Alice):
And now let me present
the third row.
It embraces the main dish.
That's a meat sushi using beef
filet, aged at low temperature.
Mmm... mmm...
THERE IT IS AGAIN!
Two kinds of umami components
are spreading on my tongue!
I see... I understand
it's inosinic acid.
Given it's a meat sushi...
but glutamic acid?
It comes from tomatoes.
Tomatoes? I don't see
any tomatoes here.
They were incorporated
into the cake sushi.
(Alice):
I used a centrifuge...
which thoroughly broke them down
into pigment, fiber,
and jus components.
I then filtered the jus
to make it even more pure...
and added a few drops to each.
Genius!
Not a trace of the original
ingredient seems to remain.
And what about this last piece?
(Saotome):
Looks like sea bream sushi,
but what's that orb?
(Judges):
Mmm.
Oooh!
This isn't an orb!
It's solidified dashi stock!
(Saotome):
It develops on the tongue...
a sea bream ochazuke!
(students in shock)
The Prodigy of
Molecular Gastronomy...
She's done justice
to both those terms,
using her skills
to continually pique
the interest
of the diner.
Such a sense
of satisfaction!
This has equaled
a sumptuous meal
served at the finest
of restaurants!
Mmm!
(Senzaemon):
From this small bento box...
a knowledge of
fine cuisine has...
BURST INTO EXISTENCE!
(Male Student 1):
HE SHOWED HIS CHEST!
(Male Student 2):
Dude, he's jacked!
(Female Student):
The director took
his clothes off!
Excellent job
there, Alice.
(pleased giggle)
(Male Student 1):
Wow! That's what
Alice Nakiri is capable of!
(Female Student):
I can't believe that girl's
the same age as us.
(Male Student 2):
I could spend my whole life
and never catch up.
(Saotome):
The light of such
prodigious skill
will create its
own shadow upon the world.
It's simple
cause and effect.
This is the renowned
Tohtsuki Academy.
Any coward who would buckle
under these conditions
is dead weight.
(Senzaemon):
Behold.
Hmm?
Five bento boxes...
order up!
There is at least one cook
who doesn't falter
in the face of
insurmountable odds.
(Senzaemon):
Soma Yukihira...
What have you prepared?
Seaweed bento!
(Male Student 1):
Did he say "seaweed"?!
(Female Student):
Seriously?!
(Male Student 2):
How could he possibly
beat Alice Nakiri with THAT?
(defeated groans)
(Male Student 1):
Seaweed bento?
(Female Student):
Is he like, mental?
(Male Student 2):
He's done for.
Hey, uh... Soma.
Yeah?
What's a seaweed
bento, huh?
Really? Wait, you
seriously don't know?
You want me to make you
a box afterwards?
The thing is, this ain't
your normal variety.
(Soma):
It's Yukihira‐style
"evolved" seaweed bento!
Please, help yourselves,
gentlemen.
Oooh!
Soma:
This here is a food jar.
It's made from
all stainless steel.
You can keep things like rice
and soup hot until ready to eat.
Wow... Japan's bento boxes have
come a long way, haven't they?
Some modern ones can
keep things nice and hot
for half a day
or sometimes more.
If you put the soup in
while it's piping hot...
it will help keep the
rice warm, as well.
Really? That's
so clever!
He doesn't even
look nervous at all!
Even though he's in
the middle of the match!
Is she talking down to Soma?!
That pasty, little tramp!
(Ikumi):
Look at that smirk.
The slunk meat thinks
she's already won this!
Alright...
let's begin.
(Judge):
Starting with
the three sides.
Mmm!
(Judge):
What a splendid isobe‐age! The
fish cakes are perfectly fried!
Thank you.
I personally made
those fish cakes
and then fried
them up for you.
He used beer
in the fried batter.
Alcohol will help volatize
the batter a lot faster.
It'll give it a texture
that isn't too gummy.
Huh? How do you
know that Ryoko?
(Ryoko):
Easy. I saw Yukihira trying out
recipes in the dorm last night,
and he let me
taste a few items.
(fish‐tastic moaning)
It's brimming with umami!
I can practically
smell the seaside!
Yow!
It seems to fairly
envelop oneself!
Um... who are you?
(Senzaemon):
Mmm...
(Judge):
This shredded burdock root is
mellow but has depth of flavor.
I have a secret.
You just have to add
a hint of mayonnaise
and balsamic vinegar.
How thoughtful!
You made this considering
the smallest details.
(Oizumi):
Wow! It is easily parted
with only chopsticks!
It was seasoned
with dashi stock,
and simmered before
going in the fryer.
That would certainly give it
this beautiful texture.
(Oizumi):
(beer‐battered laughs)
The mellow flavor of it
envelops my heart!
Like the gentle breeze of
the highlands in Spring time!
(overjoyed laughs)
Such refined
flavor and spirit!
Oizumi:
What is this?!
It seems the answer lies
in the fish stock.
I see it, now.
It was made with
maguro tuna flakes.
Exactly right.
I simmered the cod...
in maguro and seaweed
from Rishiri Island.
Maguro flakes...
Those are made from dried
yellowfin tuna, are they not?
Right. The stock is milder
than using shaved bonito,
but they have a very
delicate, refined flavor.
The maguro flakes
are the PERFECT match
for the subtle
umami of the cod.
Such an elegant dish
for us to savor!
Now to try the soup...
(Bald Judge):
Oh! This miso soup
has bacon and onions!
(soup‐er slurping)
Oooh! Unbelievable!
(Bald Judge):
The unique fragrance
of the maguro stock
permeates the nostrils.
Combined with the sweetness
of the tender onions...
it's like being hugged
on the inside by an angel!
Incidentally... there's
a trick to the soup
that makes this bento
work even better...
Just add the stock, ingredients,
and seasonings to the food jar,
and voila!
In a few hours, you'll have
a sweet‐tasting soup
with all the vegetables
cooked through.
Whoa... that is
really convenient.
Though I did put mine over flame
since we're eating pretty soon.
You do seem to be quite
knowledgeable about bento boxes.
I guess so.
I've made them before at
the family eatery back home.
But it's not enough,
Soma Yukihira.
(Alice):
Your attempts
are too pedestrian.
It may just be a bento,
but you have to make something
glamorous and surprising...
like MY perfect bento box.
Oh, yeah, that was cool!
Yours looked
super delish, alright!
You'll have to let me
try it, sometime!
(haughty laugh)
Sure, that will be fine.
(Soma):
But still... the thing
about your dish...
Are you confident that it
was a great Bento box?
What are you saying?
Did you put everything
you have within yourself
into your own creation?
(Soma):
One of our regular customers
was an old lady named Mrs. Kiyo.
She came almost every day...
but then she hurt her lower back
and couldn't come anymore.
(doorbell rings)
(Mrs. Kiyo):
Yes, be right there!
Mrs. Kiyo, hey!
Is your back okay?
Oh, Soma dear!
Isn't this when the restaurant
gets busy and‐ Ow, ow, ow!
Here... have this!
You haven't had dinner.
See ya!
(Mrs. Kiyo):
He came just to give me this?
(panting)
(Young Soma):
It was crazy slow at the shop,
so I thought I'd make you this.
Eat it, and feel better, okay?
P.S...
Peel back the seaweed...
Have a look
before you eat the rice!
Oooh...
(Present Soma):
I tried to convey something
with the bento box that day.
You should have taste.
But there should be more...
Something that lies
beyond taste.
Oooh!
What is this
magical‐looking rice?!
Whoa... Can this be...
...called a mere seaweed bento?!
Hm?!
(Oizumi):
Look at this beauty!
It's topped with some sort
of dark granules!
(Male Student 1):
The hell are those?
(Female Student 1):
Caviar, maybe?
(Male Student 2):
Salmon roe?
(Female Student 2):
They're so dark!
This is all
so mysterious...
And I MUST solve the mystery!
One way to find out!
The texture is like salmon roe
that explodes in the mouth!
(Oizumi):
The flavor of seaweed
bursts from within,
cleansing my very soul!
(Students):
Whoa!
I taste the divine
saltiness of seaweed.
It has bound it's deliciousness
to each grain of rice...
I can't take it! I could
get seriously hooked on this!
He was able to extract the
umami of the seaweed...
and used sodium alginate
and calcium chloride
to make granules. That
was quite inventive of him.
Molecular gastronomy?!
But that's...
...Alice's area
of specialty!
So tell me, how do you
know about that technique?
From Isshiki.
He asked me if
I wanted to help out
with teaching the kids'
cooking class the other day.
Huh?
I got along pretty
well with the children.
They even gave me some candy
when the class was over.
When I saw some of the stuff
they gave me, I remembered...
That I used to eat these when
I was just an unruly kid, too!
What are those?
Traditional sweets?!
Traditional?
I don't get it?
Are you kiddin' me? They call
this stuff brain fuel.
(Alice):
It contains Calcium chloride
and sodium alginate.
That just means you can make
artificial salmon roe with it.
Even made a few dishes using it.
I loved it as a kid.
Look what I made!
The miso soup is hard!
That's great!
Looks pretty cool!
But don't serve that
in the shop. Ever.
(Soma):
You see these
dark things?
There seaweed I've
changed up in my own way...
little bullets
of seaweed umami!
He used molecular
gastronomy...
through the use of candy.
Oooh... there's
something in this rice.
Such exquisite flavor!
(Oizumi):
He made a sweet, playful
filling using the maguro flakes!
This is a four‐layer rice!
If Alice Nakiri
gave us a jeweler box
of immaculate presentation,
THIS is a treasure chest of a
delight in its delicious riches!
I remember as a small child...
(Judges):
...opening the lid
of the bento box...
(Saotome):
...and that
feeling of elation...
It's all rushing back to me NOW!
My bento box even included
a sea bream ochazuke
for the final course.
In terms of overall flavor...
my bento is by far‐
Oh... please stop!
If you don't mind,
I need you to save
a third of
your rice, please.
(Soma):
There's another compartment
under the top layer
of the bento box.
Kudzu sauce?
That sauce includes three
times as much maguro flakes
and Rishiri Island
seaweed as normal.
(Soma):
I would like for you to pour
that over the hot rice.
Time for the final course!
This will most...
...definitely...
...impressively...
(Judges):
...be DELICIOUS!
OOOH! That kudzu sauce!
It's TOO delicious!
Mixing it with the
"bubbles" of seaweed...
...gives it a whole
new level of luscious!
All the judges
are wiggin' out, bro.
They're totally different from
when it was Alice's turn.
(Aoki):
It actually looks like
they're all best buds, now!
Okay, Soma...
Are you trying to tell me
that one must put one's
heart and soul
into the bento box?
Wouldn't you say being delicious
is a tad more important?
Idealism is
nothing more‐
No.
This is not considered
idealism at all, Alice.
But Grandfather!
When did he get naked?!
Look, Alice...
your bento box made
use of cold air
for its presentation,
correct?
Yes. After all, a bento box
should be served cold.
And that's what
most would conclude.
But Soma Yukihira came
to a different conclusion.
(Senzaemon):
First... he considered his
bento box from the outside...
then infused it with
a sense of flair
where HEAT was the source
of its deliciousness.
The result was this bento.
Of course, yours was remarkably
delicious as well...
But here... the difference is
that you could have served
the exact same thing if this
had just been a sushi battle.
What?
(Senzaemon):
You did nothing more
than apply your skills
toward the contents
of that box.
A bento box has a
special charm. It's unique.
This is a twist that will
advance the bento culture.
A sense of excitement
or newness toward bento...
(Senzaemon):
Would you say your cooking
had any of that?
But you're right...
it's still important
to taste good.
There's no argument
when it comes to that.
Your order is up...
Alice Nakiri.
(slurp)
(amazed sigh)
(Rich Man 1):
Ms. Alice...I trust
you're doing well.
Is Ms Erina
in good spirits?
(Rich Man 2):
Please give my
regards to Ms. Erina.
(Rich Guests):
Ms. Erina is...
(Rich Man):
Ms. Erina!
(Rich Woman):
(Young Alice):
Father! I want to go with
you to Northern Europe!
Take me to your
test kitchen!
Please, I want to
go with you! I beg you!
The latest, most
advanced techniques...
I'll come up with an arsenal
that not even Erina can beat!
(Present Alice):
I cannot lose.
Not until...
I defeat Erina...
But...
Om, nom, nom, nom!
(bento‐ful moan)
Mmm.
Hand me my BRUSH!
(calligraphic roar)
(sobbing)
(whimpering)
Huh?
This is so warm.
(saucy moaning)
In the first battle of the
first round... the winner is...
SOMA YUKIHIRA!
You're welcome!
(Yuki):
All right!
(students cheering)
Heh.
Wow, Soma!
She looks devasted!
Well, well, Soma...
I'll say this about you...
you're a peculiar one.
You did it, Soma!
Way to go! You did so great!
(door knocking)
Huh?
(Female Stage Manager):
Your battle is about to begin.
Please be ready.
Oh... uh... 'kay!
Next... it's my turn!
(Narrator):
Next time:
"Interplay of Light and Shadow."