[NARRATOR]
The Stagiaire: a mandatory
curriculum requiring
the student to leave a
"visible accomplishment" at the
venue of a professional chef.
It is a trial by fire that has
now reached a fever pitch.
[ABEL]
No, no, NO! That's not the
right timing for a suer!
Just watch.
You want to take your time,
cooking slowly to get a
"sweat" off the vegetables.
[ABEL]
See there? Don't forget what the
surface of these looks like.
Yes, sir.
[SOMA]
Man, this French cooking
is pretty interesting.
The thinking seems
completely different
from everything I know about
traditional Japanese cooking.
That's true enough.
Japanese cuisine has a
strong "hands‐off" approach,
keeping the ingredients
they use close to rare,
but French cooking takes
a lot of time and energy
to treat the ingredients.
Even making a simple fish
stock can take a lot of
time and effort to perfect.
It's the opposite of katsuo
fish flakes used in Japan...
What is it?
It's just... You really go
into a lot of detail when
it comes to cooking, dontcha?
Well it's your fault for
not knowing the basics
of French cuisine!
Don't you get that yet?!
Oh, hey there, Soma...
you've memorized the recette
for today's fish dish,
haven't you?
Right!
No problem, ma'am.
[LUCIE]
So, Soma... About tonight...
have you decided on what
you'll make for the competition?
Yeah, I've got a general idea
of what I want to do...
but it's not quite there yet.
I assume you're prepared.
This may be the last day,
but no slacking.
Ready?
[TOGETHER]
Oui, Chef!
This is it...
something only I can make.
Tonight, I will show them
how far I've come!
(Opening song)
Is it true, Chef?
The soft opening of SHINO'S
has been a success?
Are there any plans
for a third site?
(Laughs)
That's a bit
ambitious for me.
I want SHINO'S Tokyo to
be famous AND be on par
with the main
restaurant in Paris.
That's the first step
for us to take.
C'mon Soma!
Hurry up with Table 3!
Yes, sir!
Hey, Soma, help me over here.
It looks like the
guests at Table 6 are
running late tonight.
Okay, I'll do the fish for
Table 5 first instead.
Thank you very much
for coming.
Please be sure to take
care on your way back.
[SOMA]
Well, that looks about it
for the soft open.
I guess you can close down a
little early on the last day.
We're not closed
for the night yet.
Hm?
I've invited some other guests
for a private engagement.
(Door opens)
(Gasp)
[HINAKO]
Hey there, Kojiro!
What's going on with you,
Soma? Why are YOU here?
Uh, yeah... I'm here
for the Stagiaire.
What?! I can't believe you'd
pass me over for young Soma!
Why didn't you let ME help
with the soft opening?!
You forget you have your
own restaurant, idiot?
Grarr, grarr, grarr!
Wow, it's been
a while, everyone.
Hello Soma Yukihira.
I see now.
Zis is where you've come to
train for ze Stagiare?
Well, well now.
I haven't seen you
since the training
camp, have I?
You really impressed me
at the Fall Selection.
Oh, thank you!
You know Master Chapelle
took his post at Tohtsuki
when we were students
running around rampant?
Huh...
It's been quite a while,
wouldn't you say,
Master Chapelle?
Kojiro Shinomiya...
You know as a young student,
you were so full of vitality.
[CHAPELLE]
You had some apprehension
zat you had to contend
with back zen,
but I see no trace of it now.
I'm quite proud of you.
You do great zings.
Sir!
Oooh!
Please, this way.
[HINAKO]
Oh, my. Aren't you darling?
You look just like a
little French doll!
(Door opens)
Hm?
Welcome to SHINO'S, Madame.
Oh who are you calling "Madame"?
I don't need your high‐class
fancy talk... Koji‐poo.
Chef Kojiro's...
...mother!
I oughtta jerk a
knot in your tail.
You haven't come home
in years,
and now you're dragging
me to Tokyo?
I felt guilty
about all that,
so I figured I'd
bring you out here.
I don't like coming
to places like this.
Doing all right, pun'kin?
I'm good, mumsy wumsy.
I'm getting by.
Just relax and sit for a spell.
[ABEL] What are
they even saying?
[SOMA]
Whoa. That doesn't even
sound like him at all.
(Gleeful giggle)
I'm so proud
of you, son.
[SOMA]
Um ... Chef Kojiro?
Hm?
I wanted to ask you something
if don't mind, of course...
What made you choose French
cooking as the specialty you
wanted to master?
Hm.
It was quite the
celebration when I
entered elementary school.
Just that once...
My family and I played
like we were somethin'
and went to a French
restaurant in our hometown.
I practiced using a fork
and knife all week...
and I put on the best clothes
my parents were able to offer.
To think of it now, it wasn't
really that fancy of a place.
[KOJIRO'S MOM]
It's delicious, isn't it,
sweet pea?
Huh?
Oh my goodness...
This is the first time I've ever
eaten something this incredible!
French food is just to die for!
(Laughs)
[YOUNG KOJIRO]
If I became a famous
French chef one day,
my mom would be happy...
I could make her smile forever.
(Gasp) Why would I ever
divulge that to someone
like you of all people?
Huh?!
Uh, yeah, okay.
Come on, let's get
the dessert prepared.
Uh, right.
[KOJIRO]
You know that quiche I
made on your first day?
Uh, yeah, of course I do.
Did you know that most
Westerners only see burdock
as a simple medicinal root.
They're surprised to learn
that Japanese people use
it as a vegetable
and eat it all the time.
Huh?!
[KOJIRO]
They shy away from
the others too...
such as carrots and
parsley roots.
It brings to mind the
meager foods that were
eaten during wartime.
Needless to say, they are
now shamefully looked down
on as ingredients.
Is that really true?
The forgotten vegetables better
know as légumes oubliés.
If that quiche were
given a name, it would
be something like,
"Quiche of forgotten
vegetables."
There must be food that only I
can make,
one that incorporates both the
French and Japanese cultures...
there has to be.
You once asked me before...
Why did I chose to open a branch
in Japan at a time like this?
Yes?
It was to examine my base...
to re‐explore the roots
of my cooking.
Your roots?
To once again face my
cooking in the place
in which I was born.
In order for me to gain
a three‐star rating...
this is a necessity.
Hmm.
[KOJIRO]
Can you get back to
the hotel on your own?
I'll be fine on my own.
Don't go makin' a fool of
your helpless mother.
Please be careful.
Honey...
That was really fantastic.
Hmm.
(Chuckles)
Now then...
A competition?!
There's no way I can miss that!
It really is lucky
I could make it today!
I'm telling you I don't want
you here, so you need to leave!
How could I possibly leave after
you've told me about this?!
Don't be cruel!
Oh come on, Kojiro, it's only
natural she would feel this way.
I heard that Soma will be
competing for a dish, as well.
I want to watch too.
Ugh!
I see!
This will be the first time
Kojiro gets to have
a one‐on‐one battle
with Soma again!
It's a revenge match for the
Food War back at training camp!
Huh? A Food War took place
at the training camp?
Huh?
Um... Yeah I personally
have no idea
what she's talking about,
Master Chapelle.
I think she's probably just
drunk and confused, sir.
She is known for
drinking too much!
(Laughing)
(Muffled screaming)
As you say.
Hm...
A Tohtsuki observer...
So... the food that Soma
Yukihira puts out...
I guess will determine whether
he passes the Stagiaire or not.
Well now... These conditions
are a bit harsh, aren't they?
Yes. Tohtsuki is known
for difficult tasks.
Still, students are taught
ze basics of French cooking
in middle school...
but he lacks having
zat experience.
He was quite apt at
replicating the French
recipe from my lecture...
and was able to pass
Kojiro's recette challenge
presented to him
at ze training camp...
But creating a new menu item
from scratch is an entirely
different story.
[CHAPELLE]
What's more frightening is zat
he will be judged by ZAT man.
Huh?
Hey there, Wei,
are you competing too?
I am.
She was the meat manager at the
main "SHINO'S" restaurant
up until about six months ago.
Oh, yeah? Really?
Why'd she go back
to service manager?
Well, these competitions
have been going on
at the main restaurant
a couple times a month.
You see, I've been competing
for 2 years in these battles,
but my dish has
only been used once.
[WEI]
I thought to myself,
"This just won't do..."
So I went into being
the service manager
thinking that if I dealt
with the customers directly
I might get some good menu
ideas from them.
Don't worry... not one day has
gone by that I haven't practiced
my culinary kung fu.
Same here.
I didn't become
the meat manager
just because Wei stepped
aside and let me in...
and I will prove that tonight.
That's how serious everyone
takes this tonight.
The competition, that is.
Do you have that level
of resolve within you?
When I heard Chef Kojiro's
story before, I caught a
brief glimpse of something.
And now, all I can think,
is how to make it a reality.
You can talk about "resolve"
and all that business...
But I'm here to turn my idea
into something great!
The time has come now.
Begin cooking!
Oui, Chef Kojiro!
Heat a mixture of
honey and sugar...
then once it's reached
a dark color, add Madeira
and red wines.
Then add fond de veau,
and let it simmer.
Meanwhile, sauté the
ground chicken in butter
and suer the onions.
(Sizzling)
Say, uh, why do you
cook the fish like that?
Hm? Well because doing
it this way will make
the skin nice and crispy.
Huh. I've never seen
that technique.
There sure is a lot to learn
from an eatery!
Hmm...
What?
Nothing...
That'll do for now, Soma.
[ISSHIKI]
Would you mind telling me,
young Soma?
Where did you happen to learn
your French cooking techniques?
From my dad. He's my mentor.
He taught me how
to cook like this.
He said it's perfect for making
fish nice and crispy.
Now I get it.
All the things my dad
ever learned...
He combined all of it.
Everything.
All those experiences...
All those cultures...
All the techniques...
And all the emotions...
He used them to realize
his dream:
the dream of the
perfect eatery!
So what I have to do now is...
Poêlée, suer,
allumette, escalope,
déglace, ciselé,
rôti, braiser.
(Pained grunts)
(Heavy breaths)
Urgh! AHHHH!
(Heavy exhale)
I'll take the person
that I've been...
and completely destroy him!
(Cracking)
(Slow exhale)
Thank you, that concludes the
tasting of all your dishes.
[HINAKO]
Lucie... Wei... and Abel...
Yo, Soma!
You're the last one up!
You done cooking yet?
I'm sorry for the wait.
Hm!
(Gasp)
(Gasps)
[HINAKO]
He cooked a whole quail!
Mmm. Such aroma!
Soma Yukihira,
just what is that dish?
Uh, yeah, well, it's
called an oyako‐don.
Huh?
Oyako‐don?
Huh?!
[SOMA]
Oh, well I guess I, uh...
I didn't put it in
a bowl though, did I?
Still, please give it a try.
[SOMA]
I haven't learned ALL
the French techniques yet...
This is what I know so far.
Quail meat...
Usually served in French
and Italian restaurants...
but is also known to be a
staple of household cooking.
It certainly looks like
French cuisine, but...
...an oyako‐don?
Is it the combination
of quail and poached egg
that makes it 'oyako'?
Just what exactly
are you up to, Soma?
Very well,
now to begin the tasting.
Everyzing rests on what
lies on zat plate.
Will he be able to impress
the highly placed taste
buds of Chef Kojiro?
Can Soma grasp the extent
of what he's up against?
Does he know the true
intent of the Stagiaire
that he is playing in?
(All gasp)
Aaahhh...
(Grunting)
I'm having some too!
This is...
He filled it with egg...
and even risotto!
It's so delicious!
The soft, creamy egg
and the meat of the quail
perfectly complement the
lusciousness of the risotto!
What is this texture?
There are five essential
ingredients in oyako‐don:
There's chicken, and eggs,
rice, onions, sukiyaki.
I first browned the quail
in oil, and then slow‐roasted
it in the oven.
Doing that ensures the
skin will come out crispy,
and the meat rich and juicy.
I also seasoned the eggs
with salt and black pepper
for a little kick...
And then added
fresh cream to the eggs
so they would have a
nice thick texture.
The key is to get the eggs
runny AND soft‐boiled.
(Splash)
I then finished out the risotto
with milk to keep it mellow.
Then I combined the
butter‐sautéed chicken with
onions that had been sweated
for added sweetness
and depth of flavor.
For the sauce
I added honey and sugar
to make a slightly
sweet Madeira sauce,
and finished it
with some soy sauce.
I used it like sukiyaki
stock, to tie it all together.
And this oyako‐don
is what came of it.
I just reinterpreted it
by using French techniques.
But still, stuffing the
quail with something
moist like risotto,
should have caused the liquid
to leak out before the
presentation was made...
Hey, Soma,
how did you stuff it?
(Gasps)
That texture earlier!
(Chuckle)
It was cabbage.
I lined the quail with cabbage
I'd blanched in salt,
then stuffed it with risotto.
Oh, it's just like the Food
War at the training camp!
Hmmm.
(Screaming)
Kojiro made a chou farci.
If the cabbage is
expertly blanched.
It should retain the
crisp texture while still
drawing out its sweetness.
The way he tended
to the cabbage
gracefully ties the
richness of the quail
with the flavor of the
ingredients within.
What Tohtsuki's Academy
expects of students
during ze Stagiaire...
is to contribute something to
their assigned venues.
But, of course, zere's more
to it zan just zat.
Following the war, aspiring
young French chefs travelled
to France in droves.
With dreams of being
ze next big zing.
Zey wandered from workplace
to workplace,
watching all ze legendary
greats up close
and inspecting zeir every
move and seasoned nuance.
Quickly zey learned
to steal what zey saw
and instill ze techniques
before finally creating
zeir own cuisine.
It was zanks to zeir efforts
that Japan now has authentic
French cuisine
and a reputation for
culinary excellence!
Ze true intent of ze
Stagiaire is ze same
as what zose youngsters did
all zose years ago.
And zat was... to take
somezing away from ze
professionals!
You friggin' did it!
Congratulations!
Chef Kojiro, earlier today you
said you came back to Japan
to aim even higher with
your French cuisine, right?
So I decided what I need to do
is the exact opposite of that.
I've got to smash down
the familiar walls of the
cuisine I grew up with.
So in that vein,
this is the first of that...
the first new 'Yukihira' item.
And now, ze verdict awaits.
[CHAPELLE]
Will Soma Yukihira's dish
make a name for itself
as a specialty item on
the "SHINO'S" menu?
Not good enough.
It lacks quality.
At least the way it
is at the moment.
Uh?
[KOJIRO]
You can serve that in
whatever hole‐in‐the‐wall
restaurant you plan on
running in the future...
But it's a little too unrefined
to serve in a Kojiro Shinomiya
restaurant.
With that being said...
I CAN give you some pointers
as to what I'D do
to make it SHINO's ready.
What do you say?
(Gasp)
Yes, please!
[NISHIZONO]
Ahhh!
Listen up! For this,
you should use sherry vinegar.
You'll want to use the red for
AFTER you've deglazed the quail.
Sir! Sherry vinegar
is from Spain, isn't it?
[KOJIRO]
Then skim off the residue.
[SOMA]
Sir!
Yes, Soma Yukihira...
passes, sir.
[SOMA]
Wow, that was fun.
Sorry you had to stay
with me till morning.
[KOJIRO]
Hmph! Well maybe if you
didn't have such a poor memory.
Thank you so much...
Master Sir!
Cut that out! Who're you
calling "Master"?
[HINAKO] Master? (Giggles)
[LUCIE] He just called
you "Master"!
[MIZUHARA]
That's pretty conceited of you,
making him call you "Master."
Shut up! He just
did it on his own!
Someone's telling
a little fib.
It actually
made you happy‐
[BOTH]
AHHH!
[KOJIRO]
Soma...
(Whimpering)
Go get it...
A seat on the Ten,
the number one spot.
Sir!
[EXECUTIVE 1]
Now then, please tell me
how many made it through
this year's Stagiaire.
[EXECUTIVE 2]
Well between that
and the training camp...
several students
faired poorly and were
subsequently eliminated.
[SENZAEMON]
Only those strong enough
to face their own limits
will be able to overcome them
and bear the fruits of progress.
It is with them that
we look towards the future.
This is the Era of Jewels!
All right! Idiots!
Keep moving!
No more freakin' breaks!
Yes... yes of course!
My delinquent son has
become so responsible!
(Doors open)
Salutations!
And you better
mind your manners too.
I don't need you morons
bothering the customers!
Yes, Chef Kurokiba, sir!
[CHEF]
Isami, listen.
I want you to work
on coming up with
new seasonal menu items,
as well.
Yes. Thank you
very much, Sir.
It's time that I don't stand in
my brother's shadow anymore.
Swoon‐swoon!
Thumpy‐wumpy!
Thrilly‐willy!
Sparkle‐warkle!
It all becomes... TASTY!
It all becomes... LOVE!
I wish for you to enjoy,
my lovelies.
(Giggles and laughter)
[ALICE]
No. 9 has no green onions
but extra oil.
No. 8 is a mild, extra large.
No. 9's a half order of
rice plus cabbage.
No. 11 is al dente noodles
and lots of bean sprouts.
And a noodle refill
for No. 12!
How can you simply give up?!
You must listen to me, son.
It's too late for this place...
Please, chef, just let me
use your kitchen.
Promise... I WILL turn
things around for you.
Are you serious? You'd do a
waitress' job too?
Are you sure it won't
be too much for you?!
[MEGUMI]
No ma'am...
Please, I want to!
I would really like
to contribute wherever
it is you need me most.
[BALD CHEF]
Yes, indeed.
I'd say you are now worthy of
receiving my instruction...
I will share with you my
secret firing techniques.
Are you ready
for this knowledge?
Sir!
[OLD CHEF]
Mmmmm.
Wow!
I didn't think too much of
you two at first glance...
but you two have real skill!
Don't judge
a bro, bro!
Our food will put
a smile on yer mug!
Kyokusei in the house!
[WOMAN]
Oh, my!
Who'd have thought something
like this would work out?
Just changing flavors cut
back all our leftovers!
Yes, that would be the power
of just the right spice.
[CUSTOMER]
Chef, I'd like to
try another dish.
Do you have anything
exotic to offer?
Yes, sir. There's one dish
I wholeheartedly recommend
as something one must try:
That would be the
Risotto‐Stuffed Quail with
Egg, "Cheeky Youngster Style."
(Ending song)
I'm home!
Hm? Soma!
So you're the first one back?
I missed you Ms. Fumio...
It's been too long.
Hmm. Well, you
certainly look pleased
with yourself there, Soma.
Look... All these came for
you while you were gone.
Hm? Whoa! What the
heck is all this?!
It looks like they're all
challenging you to a Food War.
(Door opens)
[STUDENT]
Excuse me!
So you made it
back here, Soma.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Tetsuji Kabutoyama...
A second‐year in the
High School Division.
I'd like to challenge you
to a Food War.
You first‐years are
already in the same league
as us upperclassmen.
So‐
I will.
Huh?
But let's do it right now.
Erina!
Oh!
Welcome back, Hisako.
(Notification sound)
[HISAKO] Breaking news...
It's a Food War...
Soma Yukihira?!
[SOMA]
It's like this...
I wanna do as many
challenges as possible
to rack up all
the knowledge I can.
I want to push myself
to the limits of my abilities.
[KOJIRO] There are countless
opportunities for growth out
there.
You just need to grab them
as they are presented.
That's why you're at Tohtsuki...
to take on the world's best.
You're welcome!
(Cheers)
[SOMA]
So, everyone here today...
I have somethin' to say:
I'll take any challenge
from any one of you,
at any time you want.
Bring it on.
And if it isn't
something boring,
I'll take you on
right here and now.
Cause it's time for Food Wars!
[TOGETHER]
Everyone, you're welcome!