(Urara):
If you missed the first round.
The winner of the first bout
of the Fall Selection is...
(saucy moaning)
(Urara):
Soma Yukihira!
You're welcome!
He did it!
(delighted squeal)
(child‐like crying)
(Soma):
Look at you...
Sure you lost, but don't
be a kid. C'mon, get up.
Huh?
Thank you‐
That was pretty fun,
wasn't it?
I'm now one step closer
to being on The Ten.
Get over yourself!
You may have won, but you don't
have to be so HAPPY about it!
And let me tell you...
our battle is far from over.
I'm not giving up the
top spot at Tohtsuki Academy!
Mark my words... Soma Yukihira.
Hmph.
Hmm?
So have you learned the limit
of your abilities?
What the hell did you
just say to me?!
You're turning into quite the
expert not only on cooking
but at being
trash, too.
You do realize that you just
praised my cooking, don't you?
Listen here!
You're going to be an absolute
mess when I get my revenge!
You're asking for it,
you skank!
Must be nice...
being you.
You get to throw your little
tantrums whenever you like.
(exausted sigh)
(Megumi):
Hey Soma!
I watched your match
from the waiting room.
Congratulations!
Ah, Megumi.
You're up next, huh?
You seem to be calm
about it. Good!
You think so?
Yeah, you're right!
You know... during the
preliminaries,
the only thing
I was thinking about
was doing
the best I could.
But now...
for the first time
ever in my culinary life...
I think I just wanna
be able to enjoy cooking.
Oh yeah? Cool.
have fun
out there, okay?
Good luck!
Yeah!
(Ryo):
As always, your food
was TOO pretty.
Are you attempting to lecture
ME, Ryo? Don't be ridiculous.
I'm just telling
you the truth.
But I think you
already knew that.
And don't push it...
Save your smack talk for after
you've beaten me at something.
Urara:
And now... the second battle
of the first round!
Here come the competitors!
(crowd cheering)
Urara:
First up is the dark horse...
the winner of the
very last round
of the B Block preliminaries...
Megumi Tadokoro!
And her opponent...
is from A Block,
AND tied Soma Yukihira
for second place
in the preliminaries...
Ryo Kurokiba!
The theme for this battle is...
RAMEN!
(menacing growl)
Let the cooking...
BEGIN!
(Isshiki):
Well, that's
the basic explanation.
One last thing
to disclose to you...
the noodles will be
provided by US.
Huh?
Your battle is set
for tomorrow...
so we've gone ahead and aged the
appropriate noodles accordingly.
Choose your noodles
from among these.
Let us know
in time for‐
I'll take this one...
Here... I'll use
this wide style noodle.
You don't need
to decide now.
Yeah, whatever.
I already know what kind
of ramen I'm going to make
for the competition
tomorrow.
He already knows?
Don't worry...
there's no need
to get in a rush.
Just let me know
by midnight tonight,
and everything'll
be fine.
Yeah... 'kay!
(Megumi):
So if they're providing us with
the correctly aged noodles...
then that means I mainly
need to concentrate
on the flavor of the soup.
A delicious soup
is based on the stock,
a concentrated
KAESHI sauce...
and various flavoring
oils and spices.
They all have to harmonize
with each other,
or else you'll end up
with conflicting flavors
that ruin the
delicate balance.
The noodles that
Ryo chose are oblong
and known for their
super elasticity.
What is he
planning to make?
Wide noodles are the
tried and true choice
for rich, thick broths...
So most likely, he's using
those particular noodles
to make something
robust and pungent.
If I want to beat him...
I will need to find a flavor
strong enough to hold its own.
It's time to move forward
with my trial dish!
Nothing's working!
When I try to
make it taste strong,
the flavors start to
fight against each other!
What am I going to do?
(whimpers)
(Fumio):
Megumi!
This just arrived for you.
It's from your mom.
Oh...
(Megumi's Mom):
Dear Sweetie...
Congratulations on
making it to the finals
of the Fall Selection.
I can't be there to cheer you
on 'cause of work...
but do your best.
I'm sendin' your favorite
ingredients from back home.
Oh Momma!
(Megumi):
Wow! This certainly
takes me back!
So many ingredients
I used to use back home!
Huh?
I've got it!
I'll use the ingredients
my mom just sent me!
This is perfect!
Oh... let
me see...
That section over there
is strangely gaudy...
Oh! Soma! We're over here!
Why would they write
her name on a fan?
Kind of... bizarre.
One of life's mysteries.
(Oizumi):
Ah... Ramen...
a simple dish always made
with three ingredients:
noodles, toppings,
and broth.
Excessive demands
are being placed
on the contestants
this year.
Mmm.
Ramen became
incredibly popular
during the post‐war
Reconstruction Period.
Not only was it
fairly cheap...
but was delicious and easily
served from mobile food stalls.
And currently...
this once humble dish,
has spread throughout
the entire world.
It's unmatched
both in depth of flavor
and amount of required
preparation time.
They're to present this
in a SINGLE night!
At a major venue,
no less.
That's right...
they're being tested on their
adaptability and ability
to think on their toes.
(Senzaemon):
What strengths
will they draw on?
To what extent
will they make use
of the experiences
they've accumulated?
In the prelims, Ryo made
a seafood curry...
(Zenji):
Will he use fish again?
I wonder what he
has going on up there?
(Ikumi):
Look at that!
The stock is prepared
by using all the fish parts!
He has rockfish...
and eel
and flatfish.
His ramen has a
seafood base for sure!
Oh‐ho!
(Oizumi):
Fish innards
and shrimp heads
will give it a
robust flavor!
He cleaned them well.
There shouldn't be ANY
unwelcomed fish smells.
Ryo made a rich, fish‐based soup
just as I thought.
(Ryoko):
She has scallops!
Megumi is using their
dried adductor muscles
to flavor the
base stock with!
(Megumi):
I'll add a strained
chicken broth to this stock
and let it
simmer down even more!
(Yuki):
Wait... so does that mean...
Megumi is actually going with
the same seafood base as Ryo?!
No. They're both using
a seafood stock of sorts...
(Zenji):
But opposed to
Ryo's thick soup...
Megumi decided to go for a
lighter, more mellow flavor.
That's an
excellent choice.
But will that stand a
chance against the impact
of Ryo's soup?!
Oh, right! Megumi's
hometown is a port city.
There's no way
she can lose
when it comes to her
knowledge of seafood!
(Alice):
(giggles)
That's interesting.
It's a battle of those
raised by the sea.
That's correct. It's
a fishing challenge‐
Mm‐hmm.
Oh, I don't
think so!
Wh‐what are you
doing here?!
Whatever
I want to.
Did you just say "a battle of
those raised by the sea"?
That's right.
(Alice):
Ryo also grew up
down by the water.
(Ikumi):
A stock of Homard lobster and
shrimp shells? Seriously?!
He's using THAT
in his soup, too?
(lobster‐grinding grunts)
(Male Student 1):
What the?!
(Male Student 2):
He's grinding the
shells into powder!
(Male Researcher 2):
Down in the bar district where
the sailors get together...
apparently there's a place
that's really popular.
Yeah? I'd like
to check it out.
(chuckles)
That's not a good idea.
(Male Researcher 1):
Some ruffian would
probably rob you blind.
(Young Alice):
I'm finally out of
the shadow of Japan...
So I should eat up everything
I can get my hands on!
What's this place? Oh.
Huh?
Whaddya want?
We're closed.
You'll have to come back later
or just go somewhere el‐
Fine, then, I'll just
wait till you're open.
(growl)
Well, well, it
sure is filthy!
Oh, excuse me, would you
mind introducing me
to the cook who
runs this place?
Quit talkin' like you
own the damn place.
Anyway, the chef
you're looking for...
is ME.
Huh?
(Soma):
"The chef"?
Yep. As you can see, Ryo has
held the top spot in the kitchen
since he was just a little kid.
He's been good
for a long, long time
Yeah...
but Megumi...
(Yuki):
She's also helped out in the
kitchens back in her hometown
as a kid!
MEGUMI!
You gotta keep
your spirits up!
We're all up here
rooting for you, girl!
(embarrassed whimper)
What is that
horrible noise?
Um... my friend...
she's from the same
dorm as me. She's nice!
(groans)
How revolting.
Cooks who act all warm
and fuzzy with each other
make me wanna puke.
(Ryo):
It's a disgrace!
A chef either eats
or gets eaten...
there is no middle
ground here!
It's all about
winning and losing!
Um... you really
believe that?
Huh?
I don't agree
with that at all...
I think what's
really important
is for everyone
to cooperate and‐
The kitchen
is a warzone...
and cooking is its power!
But I guess someone
raised all nice and cozy
wouldn't
understand that.
(Ryo):
Cooking means bringing
the other guy to his knees
and enslaving him
to your superior skills!
Anyone who doesn't get that,
has no business creating
flavors in the kitchen!
Open your eyes, girl!
You guys have been fooling
yourselves this whole time.
You've made nothing
but total garbage!
Well, you are wrong.
You're the one who is blind...
at the very least,
everything I've come across...
(beeping)
has been anything
BUT garbage!
The vegetables have
been parboiled.
Now to add two types
of soy sauce...
and keep the temperature
around 80 degrees
so as to preserve
their depth of flavor.
Yes!
Look at that.
She's staying calm.
Oh, Yeah.
She's going through
all the right steps
and not wasting
any of her moves.
The key to ramen's
rich flavor is in its broth.
She's going with a lighter soup,
which will be ruined if she even
slightly muddles the flavors.
(Students):
Ooooh!
What beauty is this...?
(Senzaemon):
It's so clear,
that it's sparkles.
(Judges):
(oohs and aahs)
(Megumi):
A lot of people have
supported me along the way...
So watch
your mouth!
Don't talk
bad about them!
(menacing growl)
Yeah, that's all I really
wanted to say, so...
(Urara):
Well... we're almost
out of time for this round!
Which contestant will finish
first? Tensions are mounting!
It's good!
(Male Student 1):
What the heck?!
Look at the judges!
(Male Student 2):
I'm not sure what
this is about!
(Female Student):
What do you think's
going to happen?!
You know... one of the
highlights of ramen
is sitting at the counter,
watching the chef
work his magic!
(Zenji):
Yeah... but cooking with
the Demon of the Kitchen
standing right there
in front of you?!
Watch it, old man!
Don't go giving Megumi more
pressure than she can handle!
It's all right.
She's calm.
Seeing it up close,
it's not only beautiful
but has a splendid
aroma to it!
So the toppings
will be vegetables?
I must say, I'm looking
forward to this.
Everything's going well.
Bring it on, home‐girl!
Take this thing
and win IT!
(Students):
(shocked gasps)
(hot‐tempered grunt)
Yes... That's
the Ryo I know.
Who are you? Don't get
many chicks like you‐
Well don't you have
some crude manners!
I have a real name, you know.
It's "Alice Nakiri"!
Oh, yeah?
Hello! Aren't you gonna
introduce yourself?!
Ryo.
"Ryo"? So what's your
family name, then?
Kurokiba.
Huh? But that's sounds a lot
like a Japanese family name.
So... you've got enough
to pay for your meal, right?
'Course I do.
You'd better.
(Male Customer 1):
Man! I sure am starving.
(Male Customer 2):
What're we gonna eat today?
(Young Ryo):
The regulars are
lining up already.
There's still a bit more time
before we open for dinner,
but whatever. Let's do this.
Hmm?
What's happening?
(Young Alice):
He seems... he seems
different all of a sudden!
Line it up!
You will pay for your food
upon your receipt.
And you will do
exactly as I tell you.
Bein' a customer of mine,
means obeying these two rules.
We're friggin' open!
(Customers):
(cheering)
(Young Ryo):
You're taking too long!
I told you, doing
the MISE EN PLACE
with what we've got in the
kitchen takes priority!
It's your no‐talent asses
trying to do it all at once,
that's gettin'
us into trouble!
(salty seething)
Whatever. Get out there
and take some DAMN ORDERS!
I've had enough of you!
What's with
your attitude BOY?!
Quit talking down
to your elders, dammit!
Are you done,
meathead...?
Do you possibly think you can
put out food better than mine?
(Young Ryo):
I could fire you
and still do your job
without breaking a sweat,
you dim‐witted hack.
Please forgive me, Chef. Sorry!
All right!
The food is here!
This is the best!
I can't imagine
heading out to sea
without having Ryo's
cooking to come back to!
(intrigued giggle)
(Urara):
We have a finisher folks...
looks like Ryo Kurokiba
is ready to show!
(Male Student 1):
Whoa... what is that?
(Male Student 2):
What's he adding?
(Male Student 3):
Is that... Melba toast?
Shove this down your throat.
It's a SOUPE DE POISSON ramen.
Really? Soupe de poisson?
A southern French soup made
with a base combining shellfish
and fish parts.
What a splended idea
for a rich ramen!
Well, let's start
with the soup...
Both the tomalley
and fish innards...
their richness come
together perfectly.
Such a bold, aggressive flavor!
Now to get some of the noodles
bathed in this soup...!
No! It's enough to
make me lose my senses!
(Oizumi):
It's an avalanche of umami!
The cheese... the rouille of
aioli... and the chili peppers!
And tempura bits
that act as croutons!
I have gathered the Melba toast.
(Oizumi):
It's been slathered with
Echire butter and slow‐toasted.
(toasty crunch)
(Oizumi):
I GET IT!
The ground up shells
had been dried out
to intensify the flavor!
Glad you noticed, old man.
The flavor of this ramen comes
from the soup base emulsified
with butter and drenched in the
essence of the shellfish powder.
The umami of
that extract...
comes from glycine,
arginine, and proline,
but shellfish has the highest
concentration of any seafood.
He added so much of that
powdered extract to the soup,
that of course it became
fiercely delicious,
grabbing the souls of the
judges by their taste buds!
(eager slurping and crunching)
I understand...
The ferocity of it, is like
a blow to the head.
To this man, having
other people eat is...
(Senzaemon):
like an all‐out brawl
to the death!
This is how he's
made it this far,
by bringing others
to their knees.
How long are you gonna keep
on pontificatin', grand pa‐pa?
We're at war, here!
Very well!
(grunt)
(battle grunt)
Baring yourself without
striking a dramatic pose...!
This is quite a rare sight
for all of us to witness!
Getting ME to strip bare
through sheer brute force...
your ambition
is admirable!
(crowd cheering)
Uh. Megumi hasn't even
been judged yet...
but the atmosphere
in here has changed!
Shifted all it's focus.
Ryo's presentation wasn't just
for the showmanship...
any interest, concern, or even
relevance for Megumi's dish...
well he just... took it.
He left her nothing
to work with, didn't he?
This is going to make
things really hard for her.
She's fine.
Huh?
(Megumi):
Take the noodles
from the strainer
and imagine cutting
the surface tension...
Go Megumi!
She doesn't
seem phased.
The atmosphere
is fine.
Yes. Just
concentrating...
she looks focused
on her cooking...
Ryoko:
In a way... it's kind
of like Soma!
My dish
is ready.
Enjoy!
(Oizumi):
What an incredibly
light soup
that's beautiful
in appearance.
Still, after the previous
rich, seafood ramen,
it's looks rather
lacking in impact.
(skeptical slurp)
Mmm!
(euphoric slurping)
(Students):
Whoa...
So powerful!
This umami is a
shock to the senses!
(Female Student):
So it's not
a light soup?
The flavor is fresh, but where
am I getting the sweetness?
And this choice of
toppings tastes like...
KOZUYU!
Yes!
I used kozuyu as a model, then
added strained chicken broth
and concentrated soy sauce.
It's a kozuyu‐soy ramen!
Kozuyu...
How interesting. Kozuyu is a
local dish of the Aizu area.
It's made by using
a broth of dried scallops.
And often served at
celebratory events throughout.
You interpreted
local cuisine as ramen?
I see the scallop adductor
is the star...
while the robust heartiness
of the chicken broth
serves as
the flavor base.
And what's even more...
the concentrated kaeshi sauce
is a blend of mild
and sweet soy sauces.
(Saotome):
The flavor of the soy sauces
is a perfect match
for that of kozuyu!
That's not enough
to explain it.
Just what is the
source of this umami?!
Well, sir... it all comes
from the vegetables.
Vegetables?!
In some mushrooms plus burdock
root and green beans as well...
They were all dried and then
simmered into a simple broth.
I get it now!
Drying the vegetables
concentrates the flavor...
(Zenji):
giving it a completely different
umami than if they were raw!
All that insane flavor got
absorbed into the broth!
That seems about right.
Vegetables tend to be Megumi's
secret ace up her sleeve!
(Judge):
This unique combining
of fibrous vegetables...
Who would have thought it
could make such a refreshing
and powerful impact
in one delightful bowl?!
I'm so ecstatic that my
facial muscles won't respond!
Oh! Before you
finish the noodles...
please try that small
bowl in front of you.
(Megumi):
Just add however much
you want to the soup.
Huh?
Ooooh! This acidity
is a shock to the palate!
It makes the flavor
profile even tighter!
What on Earth
is this stuff?!
It's an Aizu dressing.
I made it with local chicken,
shredded leeks, shiso leaves,
and pickled plums.
I thought it would be sort
of fun to change up the flavor
just a little bit.
This is far more
than "changing it up"!
This not only harmonizes the
delicateness of the kozuyu,
but draws out the sweetness
of the vegetables even more!
(Ryo):
Hey, let's see
that ramen of yours!
Lemme have
some of it, NOW!
Um, okay!
(Judge):
I'm speechless.
They're both seafood‐based
ramen...
but she created such umami
using a drastically
different approach,
much lighter than Ryo's
soupe de poisson!
Well at this point...
I still can't make a rich broth
using pork or seafood.
Either I fail at removing the
unpleasant smell...
or I can't manage to get
the flavor to come out right.
It takes an incredible
amount of true skills.
But...
by using scallops and vegetables
to bring out it's natural umami,
I thought I might
retain the balance...
and make a powerful
ramen using my own skills!
You knew I'd make a ramen
with a thick broth,
so you came at me with a silly
little counterpoint like this?!
Aren't you a little box of
surprises... Megumi Tadokoro?!
Within that
slender frame,
burning silent and fierce lays
the spirit of a great warrior!
(Oizumi):
Not fearing even
the strongest of enemies,
this delicate belle raced
headfirst into a brutal
and raging battle of umami!
Come here, girlie.
Get this down your gullet!
The umami and aroma
of the ocean is overwhelming!
I feel like
I might... collapse!
I can't... I can't
believe he was able
to make something like this!
But... I still
don't want to lose!
What a fierce battle
we are in the midst of!
Both dishes presented
such strength and power!
(Oizumi):
They're the true embodiment
of deliciousness!
I'm gonna pound you good!
SOUPE DE POISSON!
I can take your thick soup
any day of the week!
My scallop and chicken stock
can squash opponents
far tougher than you, scumbag!
Scallops! Scallops! Okay?
It's all about scallops!
Lobster! Lobster!
It's all about lobster!
You got that?!
You wouldn't know!
You want a piece of me?!
I don't think so!
You don't understand how
it's better than scallops!
Scallops, you hear me?!
Scallops!
You need to take
your country ass back
I'll crush you
in the face!
You need to take
your country ass back
I'll crush you
in the face!
to wherever it came from!
Go back? You'll have to find out
before me what's the best...
Lobster is the king of the sea!
Go back? You'll have to find out
before me what's the best...
Lobster will crush you
and your stupid SCALLOPS!
it's SCALLOPS!
Lobster will crush you
and your stupid SCALLOPS!
The director
has his brush!
Who's it gonna be?
Who's the winner?!
(obsessed giggle)
Narrator:
Next time:
"The Age of Kings."