(Urara):
The fourth bout
of the Fall Selection!
Tensions are high, as Takumi
Aldini takes on Subaru Mimaska
with their match deemed
an official Food War!
(crowd stunned)
Who the hell
has a Food War
in the middle of
the Fall Selection?!
Is that even legal
to do that?
(Hisanao):
All of the necessary
conditions have been met.
The administrative
bureau has acknowledged
that this indeed counts as a
legitimate Food War Battle.
Hmm.
A true Food War battle...
knows neither time nor place!
(Urara):
Up till now, ratings
for the opposing battles
have been a cumulative score
from the five judges...
but in this bout...
each person gets just one vote.
In other words, it will be
held to the rules of a Food War.
(crowd murmuring)
And now folks...
here come the COMPETITORS!
(crowd cheering)
You got this,
brother...
(chuckles)
Must be rough,
havin' to bail out
such a no‐talented hack
of a brother all the time.
Hmm?
Pick it up.
Huh?
You're a pig, so allow me
to teach you some etiquette.
If you pick that up...
it will prove that you
accept this challenge.
This is a battle...
(Takumi):
in the manner of a DUELLO!
An Italian will always
respond to an insult.
Should I win, you'll throw
yourself to the ground
and apologize... apologize
for defiling my mezzaluna...
and for... my
brother's good name!
(Yuri):
Ah!
Hey, you two!
What's going on?
Where the heck
have you two been?!
W‐well we got lost...
So we were with
Takumi and Mimasaka
until just a
little while ago...
But no one...
(Megumi):
No one mentioned anything
about turning this
into a Food War!
Mimasaka would have planned
on turning this into a Food War
right from
the beginning.
Huh?
That's just the kind of
crappy thing he likes to do.
(Shun):
When he sets his eyes
on a student,
he'll begin to investigate
them thoroughly...
He'll than start to provoke
them and threaten them...
doing whatever he thinks
is necessary to get them
out on the battlefield.
And he's already taken
down many chefs...
99 to be exact.
Ninety‐nine battles?
(Senzaemon):
The theme will be dessert!
NOW... LET THE COOKING BEGIN!
(Megumi):
Look at their
ingredients...
they're completely the same!
I have brought documents
regarding Subaru Mimasaka's
prior Food War victories.
This is a list of what
both contestants made.
(Oizumi):
Huh? What the...?!
He's won all
his previous matches
by just making the same
dish as his opponent!
Semifreddo.
That's the name
of the confection
you and I will be making.
Semifreddo is a popular
semi‐frozen Italian dessert
that combines the
coldness of ice cream
with the fulfillness of cake.
(Subaru):
You're plannin' on makin' one
with a top layer
of crushed pralines...
followed by a second layer
of fresh cream ice cream.
For the third layer, you'll be
using a light sponge cake
to tie it all in.
Am I right or what?
Hmph. I see all your snooping
seems to have paid off.
You think you can beat me
with the same recipe?
Don't underestimate...
the ALDINI'S!
(Shun):
As you can gather... Mimasaka
is using the Food War system
as his personal plaything.
He forces his opponents
to bet their prized utensils...
And then he tramples the
chef's pride by taking the tool
that was most important to them,
and flaunts it around school.
Who does this ridiculous
fool think he is, Benkei?
That guy is
a sadistic freak.
I heard that in one Food War...
(Shun):
he took his opponent's
prized knife...
a memento of her
beloved dead mother...
all the while laughing
manically in her face.
So then... that means Takumi had
to have bet his... mezzaluna!
(Yuki):
Don't you worry, Isami!
Just look at Takumi. He doesn't
look shaken in the least!
Yeah, his movements
are clean and precise.
(Ikumi):
When making sweets,
even the smallest mistake
in measurements,
can ruin everything.
You must always remain exact
in your ingredients.
But a big lunk‐head like
Mimasaka couldn't possibly...
D'oh!
(Ikumi):
I can't believe
how meticulous he is!
It's as if he's
embroidering a tapestry!
Like a happy,
young bride babe!
See ya later... Takumi Aldini.
Next up, are some
tweaks of my own!
Oh!
(Megumi):
Something's going on!
It looks like Takumi is whipping
the whites and
yolks together...
but Mimasaka is
making his cake
by whipping them
in separate bowls!
(Eizan):
Subaru Mimasaka
thoroughly investigates
each of his
opponents.
He pilfers every last detail
of their trial dishes
to predict what they'll make
in their final presentation...
and then... he mixes things up
so as to make something one step
beyond that of his opponent.
Whipping them together
will result in a genoise,
(Zenji):
which has a refined
but dense texture.
Conversely, whipping them
separately will make a biscuit,
which expands due to
the amount of air it contains.
It absorbs syrup well
and has a velvety texture.
Y'know, mine will absorb as much
of that sweet syrup as possible,
makin' it tastier than yours.
You chose something
that would have a smooth
and gentle texture.
You've done that since
you've arrived here at school.
(Subaru):
But when you taste
these side by side,
mine will have the stronger
flavor and be the clear victor.
His strategy is to
make slight modifications
to his challenger's recipe,
giving his dish the advantage.
Thus, reducing
his chances of losing.
All right now...
next it's time
to make the syrup...
using this liqueur.
(Takumi):
He's using
limoncello?!
An Italian liqueur. It's made
from the zest of lemons.
This is a dire turn
of events for Takumi.
Normally, rum or
amaretto is used.
For him to blatantly
use something like this...
How could he possibly know
about our secret
limoncello panna cotta?!
There's a
specialty dessert
that you like to make
at your family restaurant.
I believe that dish makes
ample use of this liqueur.
That's how I was finally
able to figure out
that you were bound to
use it in your semifreddo.
(snickers)
Has he really read
my every move?
Well, I'm not done mixing
things up just yet.
My fresh cream incorporates
mascarpone cheese
to give it added depth that will
please the pickiest of eaters...
(Subaru):
just like in that curry pasta
you expertly made
during the preliminaries.
Well? How's it feel
to get shown up
by havin' your own tricks
used against you?
This can't happen!
We can't allow this
match to take place!
In a Food War, all that really
matters is the dish presented.
Subaru Mimasaka has done nothing
to warrant remonstration.
Mimasaka's only
interest is in winning.
And to accomplish that,
he will explore even
the minutest of details.
He mimics their
very personalities,
until he becomes them.
It's especially
easy for me...
to rattle impulsive
people like you.
(Subaru):
You look all cool and calm
on the outside,
but when it
comes to cooking,
you're just another
hot‐headed chef.
You have love and pride
for your homeland,
and that sentiment
always presents itself
in the dishes
you present.
I'm so happy with this!
You're exactly the kind of
person I expected you to be.
He constantly observes
his opponent,
laying them bare
before everyone...
(Eizan):
Subaru Mimasaka...
is truly the
King of Stalkers!
(Yuki &amp; Zenji):
(shriek)
This guy's even weirder
than I imagined!
In order for him to win,
Takumi must to come up
with some kind
of new technique!
How is the dude gonna
have enough time?
At this rate, he's
gonna lose, brah!
My brother has what it takes
to handle himself on the spot.
(Isami):
There's no way an Italian
man could lose at DOLCE!
He's completely
figured out the recipe
that I was
going to present.
What do I do?
Whip the eggs separately
and start over?
No... there's no time!
There has to be a way...
There has to be
something I can do!
Once I put it in the oven...
I can't make any
changes to the cake.
Should I add diced lemon
to increase the
fragrance of the dish?
No... That would affect the
texture, which is key!
Aldini!
If you don't
start baking soon,
you ain't gonna
have a cake to serve.
Gah...
Takumi just put his
cake in the oven!
If he's going
to change anything,
it can only be with the
toppings or in the sauce.
But Takumi doesn't have
any ingredients left
(Yuki):
to change things up!
I can't bear
to watch this go down!
(Takumi):
Time is limited.
I have to move forward
with the prep work.
I'm bound by the very
rails I've laid down.
(Urara):
Alright people... we're down
to the last 30 minutes!
Looks like they're
both done baking!
Huh? Check out
his cake, man.
(Aoki):
Mimasaka's is darker
than Aldini's!
(Sato):
You're right, brah.
How come?
So he turned it
into a BISCUIT JOCONDE.
Biscuit joconde substitutes
much of the flour...
with a liberal use of
almond powder for the cake.
The result gives us a richer...
and deeper sponge cake.
(Takumi):
He made another change!
The more pride
a guy has...
the more he seizes up like
a scared deer in headlights.
(Subaru):
It's scary to put out
a dish knowing you'll lose.
The same goes for
you, doesn't it?
Aldini!
(Takumi):
If I lose here today...
why did I even
come to Japan?
Brother!
You don't need to make
that face... Little Brother.
Just remember... all the
clamor of the Aldini kitchen.
Believe in what
was cultivated there!
(deep breath)
I have to do this.
To win this battle
I need to face myself...
and look at my recipes...
and exceed them!
Okay... dessert is ready.
(Saotome):
Ohhhh! It's beautiful.
I take it... this is
the semifreddo
made to eclipse
Aldini's dish?
(Bald Judge):
I must say...
the pralines accentuate the
sweet aroma of the almonds...
accompanied by a layer
of what looks to be
half‐thawed ice cream.
Each element was treated
with grace and precision.
Humph! This is a shallow idea!
One mimicking that
of his opponent.
The flavors won't
amount to much.
Well, I guess it's time
for us to have a taste.
The three layers
have differing textures.
(Judge):
That's clear simply
by inserting the spoon.
Mmmm!
The bracing sweetness of the
lemon spreads across the tongue
while the aroma of almonds
tickles the nose!
The flavors come
together perfect harmony,
not clashing in the slightest!
It's sweet but mellow!
It's conjured my
inner feminine side
wanting to frolic in fields!
I think a biscuit
jaconde works best.
It's pairing abilities
work wonders with pralines.
The rich aroma of the
almonds in the cake‐
Shut your mouth!
You have no conviction
as an honest chef!
I'm afraid I don't know
what you mean by that.
"The devil is always
in the details."
(Subaru):
That's the source
of my conviction.
I've analyzed my
opponent's strengths
and wasted no effort
in trying to win.
What's so bad about trying to
beat your opponent at any cost?
I don't want
to admit it...
(Oizumi):
I don't want to!
But it's drawing me in.
He's a scoundrel!
He's a beast!
And a charlatan!
♪He's a scoundrel!♪
(One!)
♪He's a fool!♪
(Who?)
♪He's a punk!♪
♪And uncool!♪
(That's right!)
♪I know me a tool
who thinks he's all that!♪
♪Walking like he's talkin'
And talks a lotta smack!♪
(Wooo!)
♪But I can't help but dig
on what he's throwin' down!♪
(Word!)
♪Got my emotions
runnin' circles all around!♪
(Mmm!)
♪A Punk‐ass fool!
A Punk‐ass fool!♪
This dish has reduced to me
to an infatuated teenage girl?!
It was a sublime dessert, one
that brought Aldini's good looks
into sharp relief!
At this rate...
he has no chance of winning!
(Subaru):
Huh?
Seriously? You're
still serving?
Drop the attitude. I'm a
professional chef, after all.
(Takumi):
And a guest must always be
brought his dish no matter what.
What is that dish?
(Isami):
It's different from the
semifreddo he was working on.
Yeah, you're right!
There's a wafer‐thin layer
between the cream
(Ryoko):
AND the sponge cake!
(Ikumi):
A FOURTH layer?!
Please...
Work!
Ooh!
(Saotome):
This is intense!
Like a wind blowing
across the Mediterranean!
What did you add to it?
I've eaten semifreddo
several times.
But this is...
(Saotome):
it's different
from all of them!
The flavor of the lemon
is beautifully enhanced!
(Bald Judge):
What is this golden
layer delicately placed?
Lemon curd...
English lemon curd
to be precise.
I hope you enjoy.
Lemon curd?
Lemon curd is a favorite
amongst the British royalty,
and has a rather long
and complex history.
This paste has an elegant
aroma that pairs well
with the tartness of lemon.
(Judge):
It melts in the mouth along
with the sponge cake made
using yolks and whites
beaten together.
You've added such a
beautiful, delicate texture!
It wouldn't have worked if you
chose to make a coarser cake.
I thought the Lemon curd would
lend itself well in this manner,
(Takumi):
with ingredients such as
eggs, sugar, lemon juice,
grated peel, and butter.
But it looked like you
had very little butter
left in your
arranged ingredients.
I was able to
use this instead...
olive oil.
That's no ordinary olive oil
he has in his hands.
Truly an Italian way
of thinking my good man!
The refreshing scent
of olives is a good match
for the tart
taste of lemons.
I fairly concede to defeat,
when it comes to the
semifreddo's cake.
It would have been
no match for the impact
of the biscuit jaconde's
sponge cake.
So it hit me,
I had to bet victory
on the flavor
of the lemon.
(Takumi):
If I could use lemon curd to
accentuate the lemon's briskness
and mild flavor depth...
then there's no way
I could lose...
(Takumi):
to HIS semifreddo!
To think, adding
a new twist by using
something invented
in England!
That too is quite Italian...
a display of one's
own originality!
What you're trying
to say is this...
should be called the
"Lemon Curd Italiano,"
an all‐new dessert
of perfection!
(shocked crowd)
Even under the gun
like that,
he was able to invent a
new and amazing flavor!
((Takumi &amp; Isami's Father):
Takumi... Isami...
I want you to take these
with you when you go to Japan.
It's own Aldini
Family Olive Oil.
I'm sure it will help you out
when you need it most.
How did he know? It DID help us!
(Takumi):
The moment it hit me,
I felt like a heard something.
The switching of the rails...
(rails switching)
surpassing the recipes
of the past.
Ah!
(Senzaemon):
Oizumi, sir.
It would seem
you finally noticed.
Director!
(chuckles)
Hey. What is it?
(hearty laugh)
What do you think
is so funny?
"What's funny" you ask?
You sound so pitiful
when you ask that.
I know everything about you!
Come on Aldini, wake up!
(Subaru):
Now... it's obvious when
you compare the two, right?
MY semifreddo has way
more depth of flavor!
'Cause I too, snuck in
a secret ingredient...
I added preserved lemons!
That's a condiment
common in Moroccan dishes,
made by pickling whole lemons
in a brine for several weeks.
Good thinking.
I see... the acidity and
bitterness... is now tempered.
(Saotome):
for a mellower and more
refreshing crisp flavor.
I also added the sliced fruit
and brine to the sponge cake,
the praline topping,
and the sauce.
(Subaru):
Its slight bitterness
should have brought out
the sweetness of the
semifreddo perfectly.
I had some faith
in you, Aldini.
I was betting that
there would be no way
you'd ever
give up so easily.
That you'd come up
with a twist
using the flexibility
you've honed in the kitchens!
Not to mention you always
got your lucky olive oil
right at your little
pathetic fingertips!
I just needed to think like you.
I marked out your intentions,
and the idea I figured
you'd arrive at, was an
Italian‐style lemon curd!
Look how cute you are.
You've gone in circles,
all in the palm of my hand.
I saw through
everything... EVERYTHING!
And you never
realized it!
(evil laugh)
It's so close...
Such the slimmest of margins
between the two dishes!
(Oizumi):
And yet...!
(Subaru):
There are two
things that dominate
your predictable thinking.
One is the deep bond you have
with your little brother.
The other... is a rematch
with Soma Yukihira.
How does it feel having
been robbed of them both
in one day,
you filthy mongrel?!
He's a Diablo...
(Urara):
It's unanimous, folks!
I gotta celebrate
my hundredth victory.
Thanks for being easy.
(Urara):
We have a winner!
The winner of
the fourth bout is...
Subaru Mimasaka!
(Eizan):
There you have it, everyone.
This will conclude the
first round of food battles
for the Fall Selection.
The second battle
will be held in a week.
As with the first battle...
the match card will
be decided at random.
It will be announced
later today.
That is all.
(Yuki):
I totally can't
accept this puke fest!
What's with that
creepy stalker, anyway?!
You don't need
to take it out on ME.
Poor Takumi... he must
be pretty shocked.
I would like to make
him feel better...
but what can you say
after a match like that?
Oh?
Wait up, Soma.
I'm leavin'.
(Megumi):
Huh?
(Yuki):
Really, Soma?!
You mean you're okay with not
saying anything to support him?!
(gasps)
Hey there.
Mimasaka?!
Hey, how did you
get in Soma's room?
Had a spare.
Waaaah!
Can I help you?
Yeah. There's somethin' I think
I should tell you about.
(Soma):
All right, fine.
Hang on a sec.
I'll make some tea.
Say, Mimasaka...
you eaten dinner yet?
I've got some beef stew
I made earlier today.
You wanna have some?
(Subaru):
Thanks, that would be lovely.
I appreciate it.
(Yuki):
He should punch that loser
in his stupid face, right now!
(Ikumi):
Why is Soma treating that TURD
like he's some kinda guest?
(Subaru):
That match card for
the second battle has...
been decided.
Yeah?
(Subaru):
It's gonna be Ryo vs Akira.
And me vs. you.
You got that... Soma?
I do.
So you came here just to
tell me that, did you?
Know where this is going?
Let's just make this
a Food War.
That knife you're
always seen using...
if I win, that's
gonna be all mine.
In return, I'll offer up
something YOU'D might like.
Soma Yukihira.
I know what gets under your skin
and makes you really angry.
There's no way you can look away
when someone you've
acknowledged is insulted.
That Italian guy was kinda
pitiful, don't you think?
He was utterly defeated
before he was able
to try and settle
things with you.
His future and his pride
as a chef are in tatters!
(cackles)
Well? Get angry.
I want you furious!
Don't just sit there!
Your good friend has
just been made a fool of
and stripped of his prize!
(Soma):
Yeah... it's really
too bad actually.
But...
what you did won't
be enough to crush him.
And just so you
understand...
YOU'RE the one to really
feel sorry for... Mimasaka.
What did you say?
(Soma):
I've figured out
your petty little game.
Replicating Takumi's cooking
takes a lot of skill...
Skills I don't think
you were ever capable of.
so why would you bother doing
such a worthless challenge?
(chuckles)
That "worthless challenge" beat
Takumi out of his Mezzaluna.
As a chef, I'm way above
him and any other fool that‐
No, you're not.
All you really did was leech off
of his hard work, am I right?
(Soma):
His cooking comes from
trying out new dishes,
of countless failures
before finding something
that truly shines.
I pity you. I really do.
You don't know
the true joy
that comes from cooking
an original dish.
That's how you could laugh
at a challenge like that.
All you care about is some
superficial victory
to steal others' pride.
I don't acknowledge
you as a proper chef.
I'll do a Food War.
But I want more than just that
mezzaluna you got there...
you'll return all 99 items
you've stolen so far
from the worthy chefs
you've challenged.
Hah! Cut the crap, boy.
That challenge ain't
nearly worth it for me!
There's gotta be
somethin' to match 100‐
Then if you win, I'll quit
being a chef and leave.
I'll quit... being a chef.
(Narrator):
Next Time:
"The Secret of the First Bite."