[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Popular Japanese chef
and owner of the lauded
"SHINO'S" in Paris,
Kojiro Shinomiya will
be opening his first
branch location in Tokyo.
And the anticipation level
among food connoisseurs
for the cuisine of Chef Kojiro,
continues to rise.
[KOJIRO]
Huh? I don't even have time
to sleep, much less babysit.
[NISHIZONO]
Precisely why, sir.
Chef Dojima thinks that
by sending a student
to work with your
opening staff,
you could both benefit from it.
Ugghh...
Oh I'm sure he'll be fine.
He should be more than
happy getting to help
someone like that.
After all, it's just
a small favor for a poor
chef employed by Tohtsuki.
[NISHIZONO]
He said you'd understand, sir.
[KOJIRO]
How long is he going
to hold that grudge?
What would you know
about any of this?!
You're just some poor chef
employed by the Tohtsuki Group!
Well tell him I won't
take 'em unless they at
least made it to the finals
in the Fall Selection and
even then I prefer if they won.
[SOMA]
Hey!
Hm?
Thanks a lot for taking
me in, Chef Kojiro.
Hmm...
(Opening song)
[KOJIRO] Interesting... I never
expected YOU of all people...
Yukihira.
Yeah, I was pretty
surprised about it too.
I mean, ME at
YOUR restaurant!
I can't believe I'm here
in Chef Kojiro's kitchen...
But now I've gotta
leave one of their
"visible accomplishments"
to clear the Stagiaire.
It won't be easy to improve
anything around here ...
but I'll see what I can do.
Ugh!
To start...
why don't you go clean
all the interior areas.
Huh? You haven't
finished that yet?
Hey! MOVE, dammit!
Or you're fired!
Right!
Excuse me there, Chef...
We need to start working
on putting the final menu
together for the opening.
Oh, that's right!
Why don't you hire
someone to do the
rest of the dirty work?
Considering what's
left of our budget,
we need to try and do
all that we can ourselves.
I was very particular
on how I wanted the
interior and dishware.
I mean, can't you
go ask for as much
investment as you want?
You have the
Brousse‐Poiret Award.
Almost all of our sponsors
for the main restaurant
were against
opening a new one.
There's no way
I could ask them.
Ugh! He's got way
too much pride!
And our soft open is
happening tomorrow!
Oh, sorry
about this.
We're staff from the
main "SHINO'S" restaurant
located in Paris.
We came to help out with
opening the Tokyo location
and hang around a bit
until things settle some.
Alrighty! Nice to meet ya!
[WEI]
Oh, and over
there's the head chef
of "SHINO'S Tokyo,"
Chef Blondin.
He was assistant head chef
at the main restaurant.
He acted as
Chef Kojiro's right hand man.
[SOMA]
It's good to meet ya!
Yeah, same here.
Do your best, okay?
[KOJIRO]
Hey, quit talkin'
already, people!
Hey, Soma,
get over here.
[SOMA]
Sir!
This seems like
a lot of work,
opening a restaurant.
But y'know,
I feel pretty lucky
that I get to train
here with you, Chef.
[KOJIRO]
Just shut up and lift!
What the heck is
wrong with that kid?!
He's being so casual
around Chef Kojiro!
[ABEL]
How much time did I spend
before finally thinking
I'd gotten in with him?
And until finally in the end,
he made me head chef
of the Tokyo location!
I'd never been so
moved as I was at that
breathtaking moment!
(Sobbing)
There, there. We've heard
it a thousand times already.
It seems ever since Chef
returned from Japan back
in Spring...
he's really mellowed
out quite a bit, huh?
I agree... Wasn't
he actin' as judge
or something?
You're right, he's
been a little nicer
since he's been back.
[WEI]
He answers so nicely
when we ask questions
about cooking now.
[LUCIE]
Totally!
He likes to complain
from time to time,
but in the end he actually
teaches us what we need to know
and looks out for us!
Hm?
Stop yappin' and get to work.
(Squeak squeak squeak)
[SOMA]
By the way, Chef Kojiro...
why did you decide to
open up a new restaurant?
And open it here
of all places.
I saw an article
in TohSpo...
it said it's unusual to open
another restaurant
when you're trying
for a three‐star rating.
So let me ask you...
what did you mean before?
Huh?
You said you were "lucky"
to be training in my restaurant.
It would've been easier to
clear the Stagiaire at some
mom‐and‐pop eatery.
(Sigh)
It's so I can learn
to make my Specialty.
I can't just keep
cooking the way
I always have.
I just...
I want to move forward.
And discover a new
understanding of
the way I cook.
[LUCIE]
Break time! I'm so beat!
I can feel the end
is almost in sight.
What should we do
for lunch?
Well, I guess I
could cook something‐
I'LL make us lunch.
Uh!
You're gonna cook
something yourself?!
Is something wrong,
what brought this on?
Just set the
tables, will ya?
We get to eat a meal cooked
by Chef Kojiro himself?!
[ABEL]
He's mincing chicken...
[LUCIE]
So exciting!
He's added button, maitake,
and shimeji mushrooms and
slowly sautéing them in butter.
[WEI]
Now he's just laid out a
piecrust and he's filling
it with eggs, and soymilk,
combined with white miso!
(Fumes and sizzles)
Woah!
[SOMA]
Ahh! That looks amazing!
What kind of dish
is this?
It's called a quiche.
It was originally a local
specialty of the Lorraine
region,
but it's made its way to Paris
where it's now a lunch item.
Given you probably know
nothing of the area,
I'm sure this is lost on you.
I dunno, maybe so.
But this is perfect
for a staff lunch!
I'm diggin' in!
This is gonna
be so delicious!
[LUCIE]
"Legume Magician" sorcery!
(Crunch)
[BOTH]
What is this crunchy texture
sliding down my throat?!
Ahhhh!
It's burdock root.
"Burdock"?
I'm not surprised you
don't know of it.
It tends to be an overlooked
ingredient in Western cuisine.
The crunchiness of the
burdock is a great match
for the creaminess
of the cheese.
The juicy chicken and the
accent of black pepper
complement the rest of the
ingredients perfectly.
How was he able to get
such depth of flavor
without using any bouillon?!
He managed to draw
out the perfect balance
of the sweet tartness
of the burdock's skin
and concentrated
the velvety flavors of
the chicken and cheese.
He paired an ingredient
from Japanese cooking with
a provincial French dish!
It's good enough to be
served at SHINO'S in Paris!
[ABEL]
That's the Legume
Magician for you!
Tch. Still not there yet.
(Gasp)
Alright, let's open
some wine!
Huh? We're pushing
the budget as it is!
[KOJIRO]
But this is a staff meal
that I made.
It would be a shame not
to pair it with some wine.
I've got some right here!
Fool! This
deserves better.
I'm sorry, sir!
(Girls laugh)
He can make food
on THIS level...
but it's still not good enough?
[KOJIRO]
Soma...
Uh?
There should be no doubt...
that this week will get you
closer to your specialty.
If you can do exactly what I ask
of you up till the end, that is.
Are you ready for that?
Shouldn't be a
problem, right?
Ready!
Hmph!
Hm?
Strangely, it doesn't
seem odd.
Um, what are
you talking about?
[KOJIRO]
Your chef's outfit.
I was expecting
a laugh out of it.
Hmph!
Oh well.
Time for our soft opening.
No slacking off.
Right!
So, uh, by the way...
how is a "soft open"
different from just
a regular open?
Oh yeah, well it's
kind of treated as a trial run
prior to us having
the official opening.
[WEI]
Mostly just friends and
associates who are invited.
It's a way for us to
see how the staff coordinates
during an actual service.
[SOMA]
Ohh!
That makes sense.
[WEI]
Also, it's a way to try out
some of the new menu items
here at SHINO'S Tokyo.
We'll adjust the dishes daily
according to the different
customer reactions.
Then, on the last day, the
staff will have a competition
over the new menu items.
Really?
Hey, Soma!
You've finished all of
your assigned tasks, right?
Uh, yeah.
I've peeled everything and
made a bouillon
of homard lobster,
and I got the octopus and
daikon set up in the marinade.
Very good.
Alright for now,
I'll have you assist me
with getting all my
prep work done.
Once you've gotten
the hang of things,
I might have you
support Chef Abel too.
Sounds fun! Lead the way.
[SOMA]
They've prepared three set
menus for the soft open.
Each menu will have
a different main dish
and a number of palate
cleansers to go with them.
Well... I guess having
everything you plan on making
already decided
makes it pretty easy.
[MUSTACHED CUSTOMER]
Chef Kojiro, it's been
quite a while!
Welcome, I'm grateful
to you for joining us.
[SOMA]
Welp. The first
guests are here.
I'd better get to my station.
Mm!
[SOMA]
What the hell?
Why's everyone so nervous?
(Exhale)
Dear Lord, please protect us.
We have seated guests
waiting on us.
Let's go.
[TOGETHER]
Oui, Chef!
[SOMA]
Everyone's so fast!
And so quiet...
All I can hear is the
sound of utensils and
the bubbling of pots.
(CLANG)
[KOJIRO]
No unnecessary noise.
Do that again and
your ass is out.
(Quiet sizzling)
Okay... It's so they
can be aware
of even the slightest
change around them.
(Sizzling continues)
Amuse‐bouche up for Table 1!
[TOGETHER]
Oui!
This is different
from any kitchen
I've ever experienced before.
(Twinkling)
(Gleeful squeals)
Terrific!
This lives up
to his repute!
He is indeed a magician!
Hors d'oeuvres...
ready!
Oui!
Next, Table 2.
[WEI]
We have four guests
at Table 3.
(Panting)
[ABEL]
Guests at Table 4.
[LUCIE]
Soma, don't fall behind now,
and I need that fumet de poisson
strained quickly. Hurry, now!
Ma'am!
There's so much to do.
Even with all the prep work,
there are still
so many more steps
compared to a simple diner.
And you have to make
the appetizers
WHILE you're
prepping the main dish,
which already takes up
most of your time.
Look, Soma, the langoustines.
Uh! Oh yeah, a "langoustine"...
Scampi!
Right here!
I need you to prep the mirepoix
when Table 3 is done eating.
Mirepoix... A medley of diced
flavoring vegetables.
Dammit! It's taking too long
to figure these things out!
But I'm still
keeping up so far.
Table 3 has just
gotten their appetizers.
I'll prep the fish first,
then move on to the mirepoix.
(Gasp) Hey, Soma!
Where's the mirepoix?
The plates for Table 3 are
already back?! Oh, crap!
I'm sorry!
I'm working on it!
[SOMA]
In full‐course meals the
next dish is brought out
at the moment everyone
at the table has finished
the previous one.
That means you have to gauge
when to serve the next dish
based on how fast
the diners are eating.
And there are multiple
tables with different
arrival times for everyone.
You can get prepped
for one table,
but then another table is
breathing down your neck!
Hey, Soma. Get on that
mirepoix right away.
Lucie, put Table 3
on the backburner.
Get Table 1's fish out
to them first!
Oui!
Wei, table 3's meat
looks to be
about five minutes
behind.
Let our guests know.
Oui!
[KOJIRO]
Abel, go clean up after
all of Soma's mistakes.
[ABEL]
Oui, Chef.
I'll go take over
for Table 1.
Move it.
Yes, sir.
Not only did I not help Abel,
but I actually cost him time.
Up till now, even if I've
fallen behind,
I've always been able
to make up for it.
But it's different here...
now if I fall a little behind,
it not only affects me
but everyone else around me.
I'm just going to say
this up front:
I still don't acknowledge you
as a member of our Shino's team.
No don't!
You got something to say?
There's no place
in the kitchen
for someone who
causes delays.
[ABEL]
I'm the head chef
of "SHINO'S Tokyo."
I oversee
everyone's work.
You get it now?
You're nothing
but a stagiaire.
[ABEL]
Don't just think you can
force your way into our ranks.
If you understand, keep your
position in mind and‐
I'm sorry,
I'll get back to work!
Uh?
Hmm.
[SOMA]
The soft open runs
for five days.
I can't be like this
the whole time!
Sorry for the wait!
Before this is over...
I WILL be a useful
part of the team!
(Dramatic, uptempo music)
Why aren't the ingredients
out yet?! Hurry up!
I'm sorry!
This is a disaster.
You fail!
Huh?!
You failed!
Get out of my sight!
Ahhh!
[TOHTSUKI JUDGE]
You fail!
(Gasp)
[ABEL]
Feel free to use the
shower room whenever.
The kitchen staff will start
showing up around noon.
Until then, you'll be
on your own in here.
Be sure not
to oversleep.
Yes, sir.
From what I witness of
your performance today...
I'd be more grateful
to not have you here.
[KOJIRO]
My success here in Japan
all depends on how this
soft open goes.
You must feel pretty
carefree just getting to
be a student at this time.
Am I right?
From this day on, we have
even more guests expected.
You'll have two to three times
more workload than today.
The way your presence is working
out for us right now...
there'll be no place for
you come the final day
of our soft open.
(Door slams)
[WEI]
Chef Kojiro...
are you not going to try and
give him just a little advice?
I can't go around holding his
hand at all times, can I?
Besides...
[ABEL]
Uh...
No, it's nothing.
[LUCIE, FLASHBACK]
Soma, don't fall behind now,
and I need that fumet de poisson
strained quickly.
No, no, no!
These have to be sliced
allumette for this recette!
Do it again!
Do that again
and your ass is out.
[SOMA, FLASHBACK]
Is it delicious or not?
Say it!
[SOMA]
Order up!
My food...
How do I find food
that's uniquely mine?
Hmmm...
There are three different
methods of cutting the
potatoes for the recette...
pont neuf, allumette,
and paille.
Each cut is a different length
and thickness.
Cutting methods for fish are:
médaillon, darne, tronon,
and escalope.
They're used according to
ingredient and cooking method.
Good morning, Abel!
Hey. 'Morning, Lucie.
Uh. Hey, good morning, guys.
(Gasps)
Soma, you're
here early.
Um...
If you don't mind...
I had some questions
about the ingredients
I cut incorrectly yesterday.
Do you, um, have a
little time to talk?
No, right now, you clean
and prep the ingredients.
Don't you think you're being
just a little too cocky
for someone who dragged us
all down yesterday?! Well?!
We're not going to waste
any more of our kitchen
time just because you‐
Abel!
Huh? Oh...
[ABEL]
All the cleaning,
the peeling...
It's already done?
Hey, Lucie, please answer
any of Soma's questions.
Oh, sure!
[LUCIE]
What do you want to know?
[SOMA]
Thanks. It's about the
difference in the cuts.
I know that médaillon and darne
go pretty much like this...
Did he actually do
all of this work
single‐handedly?
(Soma continues)
How could he?
He must have barely slept.
[LUCIE]
Oh, tronon goes like this.
It's a bit tricky at first.
That's no good!
Do it again!
Sorry! I'll have it soon!
Do it in twenty seconds.
Sir!
Hey Soma, the sides.
Sorry! I'll get to
those after this.
That's not really considered
an hors d'ouvre, per se.
Well, how about used
as an entrée?
Too long.
Speed it up more.
Sir!
[ABEL]
Not again? That's the
third day in a row.
I'm really sorry for
bothering you.
I just wanna learn
everything I can.
So today I only have about
55 things I'd like to
ask you about, Chef.
(Crack)
Would you like me
to answer all those?
[SOMA]
Um, it's about this.
Oh! It looks like
it's done
just how I showed
you to do it!
There are three or four things
I'd still like to work on.
[LUCIE]
Like what?
That boy...
[ABEL] No, no, no, no, NO!
Every day, I reprimanded
so many times...
[ABEL]
But he still seems so
indifferent from my
harassments.
(Questioning continues)
I've been making it
painfully clear for him,
just how out of his league
he is here.
So why won't he
cave in already?
(Uplifting music)
Yes... that's correct.
Tomorrow will be the
last day of our soft open.
Finished.
Hey, Soma!
You were lookin' for the
fish for Table 8, right?
I got it prepped already.
(Gasps)
Merci!
I've finished breaking down the
rockfish.
Can you check it for me, please?
[SOMA]
I've finished deglazing
the suyuk.
Here's the champignon tourné.
Can someone gimme a check
on my minced shallot?
Perfect! That's good!
[LUCIE]
Soma, Table 6 is up.
[SOMA]
Got it!
I don't have a second
to be discouraged.
Because right now...
mastering these techniques
is everything!
And it's so much fun
I can't stand it!
[ABEL]
I can't believe he's
absorbing all this...
and with such incredible
speed and skill!
Table 4 is scarfing down
their food really quickly!
Can we hurry up
with the soup?
Urgh! I haven't done
the prep work yet!
Abel, can you get on it?
Sorry, I can't seem to
get away right now, Chef!
My hands are full too!
I've finished up
all the prepping.
(Gasps)
[KOJIRO]
Soma.
I assume you've
memorized the recette.
Go ahead and finish
it out for us.
(Gasp)
Yes, sir!
[CUSTOMERS]
Man, I can't get over how
delicious everything was.
I'm so glad we
were able to make it.
I'd like to bring a
few friends next time.
The Chef really outdid himself.
(Sigh)
Good job, everyone!
[KOJIRO]
The soft open ends tomorrow.
Don't go slacking off
on your last day here.
Understand?
Of course not!
(Chuckles)
You did really great!
I'm so proud!
Thanks a lot!
Hey, Abel. Do you have
any objections with
Yukihira staying?
(Scoffs)
I don't.
Well, I guess he gets
a passing grade after all.
For a while, I was worried how
things would turn out for him.
He didn't get a
single word of advice.
It means nothing if you don't
overcome on your own.
Besides...
Um, excuse me Chef.
There's just one more thing.
What is it,
Monsieur Yukihira?
Do you have another complaint?
Does that rule at Tohtsuki
still apply after a student
has already graduated?
What are you talking about?
I'm challenging you.
(Gasp)
If I beat you in a
Food War challenge,
will you take back your
decision to expel Megumi?
(Megumi whimpers)
[KOJIRO]
You are the man who dare picked
a fight with me, of all people.
I doubt you're a chef who'd be
done in by the Stagiaire.
(Slam)
[SOMA]
He beat me...
And I...
I lost.
Hm!
Dammit...
[SOMA]
Chef Kojiro.
Excuse me...
you have a quick second?
Yes, what is it, Soma?
Do you have a complaint?
No.
Since it looks like I've
made it to the last day,
I have a favor to ask.
What now?
The battle...
(Gasp)
If I could...
I'd like to enter the
competition tomorrow
for the new dish.
I have something
that I'd like to submit.
What?!
The competition?
But you had your hands
full just trying to support
all of us back here.
Uh!
You know, Soma...
Oh come on.
I had always planned
to submit something.
I've been putting an
idea together in my head
the past few days...
but now I'd like to make
it happen for real.
(Gasps)
Are you sure you can put out
a worthwhile dish?
I am.
And as you said...
this would be the first time you
get to taste your recette, yes?
That's right.
Very well.
However...
Don't come crying to me if your
budding self‐confidence
withers under pressure!
[SOMA]
I will make them
something great.
Something only
I can make.
My...
specialty!
(Ending song)
[NARRATOR] Next time:
"Pomp &amp; Circumstance"