[SOMA]
I'll quit...
being a chef.
If I lose in a Food War to you,
I will never represent
"Yukihira" again.
You have my word
I'll never stand in a
professional kitchen again.
Tell me... is that enough
for 100 items?
[MIMASAKA]
(Gasp)
I tell you what
I'll even make things
a bit easier for you.
The theme for the second battle
is Western food, isn't it?
Here ya go...
I'll be making THIS.
[MIMASAKA] Huh?
[SOMA] Beef st‐
[IKUMI]
Are you an idiot!?
Shut your flapping hole!
[YUKI]
Don't just tell him what you're
going to be making, dummy!
Why not? He's gonna
find out anyway.
And giving up being
a chef if you lose?!
What's your deal?
You're a disgrace!
Was cooking never more than just
some hobby you could toss aside
whenever you felt like it?!
Meat Meat...
[IKUMI]
Don't call me Meat Meat!
[YUKI]
But wait!
[MEGUMI]
Are you serious?
[SOMA] 'hmh?
You would really quit
being a chef?
Just getting Takumi's
mezzaluna back would be
more than enough to‐
That's not enough...
[BOTH]
Huh?
I want all 100 items
you've stolen up until now.
You'll return them to
their rightful owners.
Even if it means betting
everything I have as a chef...
I WILL defeat you...
Subaru Mimasaka!
Then it's settled little man.
It's a Food War!
[HISAKO]
Dearest Miss Erina,
I suffered a humiliating defeat.
As such, I have no right
to show my face to you.
I ask that you please
grant me leave.
[ERINA]
Hisako...
You never asked what I thought.
[SOMA]
Beef stew, beef stew,
beef stew, beef‐
(Doorbell rings)
[MITSURU]
O‐M‐G, Soma Yukihira?
I do not believe this!
This is so amaz‐!
(Cracking)
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Oh man, why would
you do that?!
Ah, sorry about that.
I thought you were
one of Mimasaka's spies.
No, my name is
Mitsuru Sotsuda.
Um, I'm a 3rd year in the
Middle School Division.
And I'm in the
Journalism Club!
[SOMA] Oh yeah...
The Journalism Club, huh?
(Gasp)
The whole school
can't stop talking
about you and this
gamble you're making!
So well I have a favor to ask!
Will you let me
shadow you for the week?
I wanna write a story
on everything leading up
to the Food War.
Huh?
I was so moved when I
saw you at Fall Selection!
You're really somethin'!
I'm still considered
kind of a nobody in the club
so they won't give me
any major articles yet...
but if I get in on
a story like this
and knock it
out of the park...
I think I'll be able to make it
as one of their top reporters!
[SOMA internal]
I just wanna COOK!
Wait, please sir, Soma sir!
No way.
What? No! Please!
I promise it'll be great!
Just gimme a chance!
[MITSURU]
Please Mister Soma sir! Please!
Please let me write
about you. Please!
For the love of
all that is holy...
please let me do it!
I'm begging you...
PLEASE!
[GIRL]
What's that about?
[OTHER GIRL]
I guess it's like THAT?
[GIRL]
But you like that sort
of thing, don'tcha?
[MITSURU]
Oh God, you are the best!
I promise you're not
gonna regret this.
The others have to attend
workshops in the afternoon.
It'll help to have someone
taste my stuff objectively
and give me some tips.
So you're going to be
experimenting with your
beef stew, right now?
I believe there are two
focal points in a beef stew...
the cut of beef to be used
and the demi‐glace sauce.
Sounds simple but I know
there's more to it than that.
Some places specialize
in just this stew.
I hear they spend
two weeks on the sauce...
just letting it simmer down
that whole time.
Unbelievable!
So... I'm assuming
you chose this dish
because you're confident
you'll be able to make
it in a short time?
Hmm... Whether I'm confident
or not is besides the point...
Ultimately it comes
down to taste!
(Grinding)
(Sizzle)
As you can gather by now,
this process will
give the finished dish
a much deeper flavor.
Once the meat's got
a good color goin',
you simmer it in stock and
some bouillon till it's tender.
Then you bring it to a boil,
and skim the fat out.
It already smells
unbelievably delectable!
If you bundle parsley, thyme,
bay leaves, and tarragon
into a petite bouquet garni...
it makes it easy to remove
the aromatics when done.
[MITSURU]
Oh! What a lovely color!
The key is to strain your
demi‐glace once it's simmered.
That will improve
the overall flavor.
Then just season it with some
salt and pepper and voila.
It's really not to terribly
difficult to cook.
Okay... it's done!
[MITSURU]
Wow! It's so rich!
The beef is so shiny and
looks absolutely perfect!
I can't wait to taste it!
Okay, now for a bite...
The chunks of meat
are so thick...
and yet they fall apart
just by using a spoon!
Aaah...
(Chomp)
Mmm...
The moment it enters the mouth,
the meat just melts away
softly on the tongue.
Its juices explode
with each new chew,
mixing in with the demi‐glace
in a vibrant dance of life!
(Swallow)
Exquisite!
I usually think of beef stew
as being really acidic
and tough to chew.
But yours is somehow
so mellow and tender.
Did you notice?
My secret ingredient
is white miso.
The trademark acidity in a beef
stew comes from adding tomatoes.
As you see some people
don't care for them very much.
Adding white miso at the end
while it's still simmering
will allow for the acidity
to mellow out some.
Making something more
in line with what
Japanese people prefer.
Amazing!
I remember comin' up
with this...
I was a 2nd year in
middle school, at the time.
I was up late trying to work
on an off‐menu item.
This was the first dish of mine
that my dad said was good.
Whoa! You could easily beat
Mimasaka with this dish,
don't you think?
It's really good.
Nah, not even in the runnin'
This is the exact same thing
I served to him yesterday.
Wha?!
Wait, why would you do
something like that?
Well... He would've found out
about it eventually anyway.
Plus, I wanted to try and
level the playing field
for us a bit...
I guess you'd say.
This was the best thing I made
before I came to Tohtsuki.
But how far have I evolved
since then, and is it enough?
And will this make Mimasaka
try even harder to try
and replicate my dish?
That flavor is just
the starting line
for this competition.
This is gonna be...
a battle of imagination!
[AKIRA]
Soma and Mimasaka, huh?
[RYO]
The only way to find a winner
is to throw it down in
a fight to the finish!
[SOMA]
Still no good.
I added some cumin and cardamom
to flavor the meat...
like I learned from
making the curry...
but the aroma is
all off on this.
The demi‐glace is
coming off as too potent.
Adding spices while it's
simmering makes it too strong
while at the same time the
mild flavor is way too sharp.
I thought about completely
changing the flavoring agents...
but if the white miso
loses its mellowness,
the dish becomes
something different.
I've tried different ideas...
but I can't seem to find
just the right one.
In my Food War against
Meat Meat,
I had to combat A5‐grade beef.
Then, in the first battle,
I needed to beat
molecular gastronomy.
My thinking so far has been
to use my opponent's
specialty against them...
but Mimasaka's an
entirely different breed.
It's like I'm being
chased by my own shadow.
Hey, Mitsuru...
for the next trial dish‐
I'm way too full
to eat more.
Did you really finish
each and every dish?
I couldn't possibly leave
any of that uneaten,
that would be a waste!
(Burp)
It's no good.
I know his heart's in it,
but something about him
is not working.
Is there anyone with a good
sense of taste I can use?
[ERINA]
"You want to...
walk home together, Sachiko?"
"Huh?"
Wait! They only met
a few months ago
but they're already
walking together... ALONE?!
It won't be long before
they're holding hands
and whispering sweet nothings.
How lewd of them!
Ugh! I don't have the next one.
They can't just
leave me like this!
Hisako!
Where's the next issue?
Oh. That's right...
[ALICE]
Are you serious?
Don't tell me there's no one
you have feelings for
even though you're in
high school surrounded
by gorgeous boys.
You really are completely
hopeless aren't you?
[HISAKO]
When it comes to
learning about love...
girls' manga are the
bible for society at large.
Thank you so much, Hisako!
Hisako always made sure to do
all the legwork for me.
If I wanted something...
she's always been by my side.
(Doorbell rings)
My sweet Hisako!
I knew you'd come back!
I just knew it!
I've been waiting for you!
(Camera clicks)
[ERINA] Ugh...
Hey, if you're free,
wanna taste something for me?
U‐uh...
Soma Yukihiraaaa!
She has such a glorious smile.
Yeah! It's a good thing it looks
like she was welcoming us, huh?
I'm NOT welcoming you.
What are you doing here?
Where's my security?
Oh. I ran into your cousin and
Ryo comin' out the front gate.
She said it was alright
if I went in.
Alice!
How incredible! To think
you could have Miss Erina,
the legendary "God Tongue,"
taste your food!
I heard you two
are pretty close,
that you ride in the same car
and talk all the time.
(Taunting)
Enough of this nonsense!
Listen here...
There are strict guidelines
you must follow.
First you must be judged
whether you're suitable or not
and you'll also have to pay
a quite sizeable contract fee!
That's how precious my taste
evaluations are, understand?!
Are you serious?
Hey Mitsuru,
how much have you got?
Huh?
You want ME to pay?
How could your pathetic
pocket change possibly be
enough for my palette?!
Well in any case...
I have no time to waste
with you right now.
I'm very busy at the moment.
You aren't busy...
you're reading manga.
Uh?!
Stay out of my freakin'
business Soma Yukihira!
You know I think someone
at Kyokusei Dorm is reading
that exact same manga.
All of them.
[ERINA] Mm...
[SOMA]
Still, if your answer's no,
then that's that.
Wait right there!
(BOTH)
Huh?
Um... well... I guess I uh...
I'll make an exception today
and have a taste.
I'm feeling charitable.
Huh? But we don't
have any money.
Money is not the only form
of compensation I seek.
There's always room
for some negotiation.
Yeah?
However... given the situation
I won't be able to
give you any advice.
I can only gauge the flavor.
[SOMA]
Well, if you don't mind.
I simmered the beef with
a bouqet of aromatics.
The demi‐glace is homemade too.
The secret ingredient is‐
It's white miso.
(Gasp)
Please remember who you're
talking to here.
I can tell you that much
without even tasting it.
[MITSURU]
Oh wow!
She is definitely the
God Tongue all right.
So how is it? You like it?
It's super great, right?
I was so moved when I took
my first bite that I almost...
It's not good.
[MITSURU] Huh?
This may do for some
common walk‐up food truck
out in the sticks somewhere...
But you're here competing in
a contest of fine dining.
This isn't even close.
It's a joke really.
You don't have a chance.
You don't understand
this theme at all.
Well... it's time you
take your leave now.
[MITSURU]
Please wait!
Miss Erina, what did you mean
when you said that?
How can you say that this
beef stew isn't even close?
[ERINA]
I've given my findings.
You draw the conclusion...
(Sigh)
I have nothing more
to offer on the matter.
Toodle‐oo.
[MITSURU]
Aww...
[SOMA]
Hmm...
(Door opens)
Huh?
About my compensation
for suffering through
your sub‐par dish...
I suppose lending me the
next volume of this manga
will suffice enough.
I'll let security
know you're coming,
so just hand it over
to them at the gate.
Yeah, thanks so much.
[MITSURU]
(Sigh)
I never thought she would
just totally dismiss it
right off the bat.
I thought it was so delicious
I could have eaten a
hundred bowls of it,
I mean I've never had
anything like it.
Yeah, that was rough.
She really tore it
a new one, didn't she?
All she did was
criticize it...
And she didn't even
offer a single hint
or word of advice
to make it better!
Oh!
[SOMA] I'm not so sure.
Huh?
There's something Erina said...
It struck a chord with me...
(Chatter and laughter)
Hey Soma, another one please!
Today's special was
really delicious!
Soma!
[MIMASAKA]
Here ya go. Eat up.
Oh!
Wow!
Your order is up!
[CUSTOMER]
Oh, that is so good!
[OTHER CUSTOMER]
Thanks for the food, man!
Welcome!
[MIMASAKA]
I'm Soma Yukihira.
My dream is to one day
surpass my father
and take over as chef
of this place.
This is off‐menu item number 5
at our Japanese eatery...
"Yukihira" beef stew!
(Foodgasmic gasp)
It's delicious!
[TOMITA]
I feel so young!
[MIMASAKA]
First thing I gotta do is beat
the snot outta this FLAVOR!
[MIMASAKA]
This was the best thing I made
before I came to
Tohtsuki's Academy...
You're welcome.
[MIMASAKA]
But how far have I
evolved since then,
[MIMASAKA]
and will it be enough?
[EIZAN]
Heh. Back to his image training.
[MIMASAKA]
It's a battle of imagination.
[EIZAN]
He does it every single time.
Well then, Soma Yukihira...
how will you combat this?
[SOMA]
(Frustrated sigh)
[MITSURU]
U‐um, Master Soma sir!
How about we lighten the mood
a little bit, huh?!
Look, the latest issue of TohSpo
published an article on the
upcoming semifinals.
Oh! Chef Dojima and
Chef Mizuhara are coming...
even Chef Inui
is going to be here.
Haven't seen them in a while.
Speaking of, Master Inui's
challenge at the training camp
was a creative dish that
centered around Japanese food.
It's kinda similar to
this challenge, huh?
(Door opens)
Hm?
[SOMA]
Uh.. Meat meat?
What's up?
Is something wrong?
I brought you a present.
I mean, since you're in
Bowl Club and everything.
But it's not like you've got
my support or anything okay.
I just don't want that
big jackass to win.
He's a complete waste of space.
That's so sweet...
Meat Meat.
Shut up! I just said I'm not
doing it for YOU, all right!
Anyway, there's no way I'm gonna
let you lose to that A‐hole
and have you not become a chef.
Understand me?!
YOU CANNOT LOSE!!
Whoa. There's a sirloin and
filet... and even some rump.
It's an assortment of
different premium cuts.
That's our Meat Meat all right.
They're all top quality.
There's some interesting
items in here as well.
But I'm not sure
I can use these.
If I used this meat
to make a stew...
(Gasp)
[ERINA]
You don't understand
this theme at all.
Are you okay, Soma sir?
Is there something wrong?
[SOMA]
I really am grateful
to you, Mitsuru.
I'm glad that
you were here.
Yeah?
But...
no more information for you!
[MITSURU]
Ahhhhh?!
Huuhh?!
Aw, come on!
Don't be like that!
What about my in‐depth
article on you?! Soma, sir!
(Music plays)
[KOJIRO]
But still...
it seems a bit unseemly
for Tohtsuki Resorts'
Executive Chef
to personally go judge
something like this ...
I didn't know you had
that much free time, Dojima.
Haha... I have a vested interest
in nurturing these students.
I must answer the call of duty.
After all, I am but a poor chef
employed by Tohtsuki.
...Right?
[KOJIRO]
Quit holdin' a grudge
against something I said
when I was angry.
[GIN]
Words can hurt, Kojiro.
Words can hurt.
Hm... Give my best to
Mizuhara and Inui okay.
(Music playing)
[MITSURU]
I wonder if he's all right?
It's about to start,
and he's still not here...
Where could he be?
Ah! Master Soma Sir!
Thank God you were able
to make it in time!
What the heck
were you doing?
[SOMA]
Sorry about that.
I had to do something.
So... did you‐uh...
did you come up with an idea to
beat Mimasaka's copycat cooking?
[SOMA]
Mmm... Dunno.
Huh?! What do you
mean you don't know?
I've done everything I can.
Now all that's left is...
just to have some fun
cooking out there.
Brother...
You doin' okay?
I was just talking to Soma.
He asked me to
give you a message:
"Be sure to watch my match."
(Loud cheering)
[URARA]
And now... Soma Yukihira!
The first bout of the
Fall Selection semifinals...
is once again being held as an
unprecedented official Food War.
A lot is at stake today,
as Soma has bet nothing less
than his career as a chef!
(Loud cheering)
Next up... is Subaru Mimasaka.
Will he come out firing
with another perfectly
recreated dish?
Now to introduce our judges,
five graduates of
the Tohtsuki Academy
and all former members
of The Council of Ten!
I'm Tohtsuki Resorts'
Executive Chef...
I'm Gin Dojima.
We shall judge firmly but fairly
on what we are presented today.
For this semifinal,
it's Soma Yukihira...
vs. Subaru Mimasaka.
Let the cooking begin!
(Gong rings)
(Loud cheering)
Hm! They're both presenting
a beef stew?
I don't care too much
for that big guy
who stuck his gum on
a cooking blade...
but that one with the headband
works in an eatery downtown?
He barely even transferred into
the Academy six months ago.
Not a chance.
I mean you agree with me right?
Yes. I think it would
be quite hard for him
to actually win here.
[GIN]
That may very well
be true ladies.
It'll take a special
stew to win this.
I'm afraid an eatery's
concoction could be
way off the mark.
[ERINA]
The allure of eatery fare...
It is said that the best
flavoring will allow the diner
to discover its true
glory by the third bite.
Until then, one doesn't know
exactly what they're eating.
If done well,
patrons can visit every day
and never grow tired of it.
[GIN]
Whereas the flavors at
a high‐end restaurant
make one think a dish
is delicious from
the very first bite...
requiring a taste that is both
powerful and memorable.
[GIN]
Simply put, this inparticular,
calls for a "forceful" dish,
one that has
unforgettable impact.
[ERINA]
And yet, Soma's beef stew
is far too gentle for
this level of competition.
And what's more absurd...
is the idea to retain the
mild taste of the white miso.
That only takes you
further away from the
intent of this challenge.
Today, Soma Yukihira
will surely show us...
a pitiful and embarrassing
loss to remember!
(Gasp)
Look at that meat Soma's
started preparing...
It's oxtail!
(Gasp)
(All gasping)
Looks like he just turned it up.
It would seem Soma
has found his own answer.
[ERINA]
Oh my god. I can see
your idea... your intent.
Oxtail is known to have
the most gelatin of
any part on the cow's body.
[RYO]
All he needs to do is add salt,
pepper, and flour to the
parboiled oxtail.
Sauté the surface to a golden
brown then let it simmer.
That way, it will impart
all that gelatin when
mixed with the demi‐glace.
and wreck the senses
into submission.
[ERINA]
The thickness of the gelatin
will bind itself to
demi‐glace or dashi stock,
adding depth of flavor
while retaining that
of the white miso.
That's smart.
That's the same method
Hisako used
for her soft‐shelled
tortoise burger.
[AKIRA]
The spice he added to
the meat was clove...
which has a sweet and
powerful flavor,
that's hard to beat.
Adding to that... clove is sure
to increase the mellowness
of the stew and
enhance its umami. Hm.
[ERINA]
Also... that vegetable
combination is a matignon.
Not a bad idea.
Look there!
He's going to take minced
carrots, onions, and celery
and sauté them all in butter
until they're tender.
You can also simmer
in Madeira wine.
That technique can be used
in different dishes...
it helps to impart the
sweetness of the vegetables.
(Pan sizzles)
[ERINA]
Uhh... That stew is going to
be even more delicious
than the one he
presented last week.
[SOMA]
What's needed here
isn't some gentle flavor
that you can just eat
bowl after bowl of.
Meat Meat's gift
ended up being a hint.
With this, I can make
a powerful stew,
one where meat plays
the starring role!
You said I didn't
understand this theme...
You'll eat those words!
Erina Nakiri!
(Smug laugh)
Huh?
(Cackling laugh)
[MIMASAKA]
Everything you've
done this week...
what you've bought...
who you've met...
and what dishes
you've all tried out...
I know about it all, Yukihira!
(Gasp)
Mimasaka too?!
Oxtail!
[AKIRA]
For spice... he's added
cloves and black pepper.
[MEGUMI]
He has a matignon too?!
It can't be!
[ZENJI]
They're the same.
He's following Soma's cooking
sequence to an absolute T!
Now... here's where
you fear me...
And I overtake you!
That‐that meat is...!
[MIMASAKA]
Here's my twist!
[NARRATOR]
Next time:
"Morning Shall Come Again"