[KUROKO] It's your turn
to answer now, Sissy.
What would you do if
there was a clone of you
wandering around the city?
[MIKOTO]
That's a good question...
Honestly,
I would probably think it was
a little creepy and not want
to hang out with her at all.
You know what I mean?
[ACCELERATOR] That concludes
today's experiment.
[yawns]
[ACCELERATOR] I made
quite a mess this time.
I wonder how long it'll
take them to clean it up.
Eh... who cares?
I should stop by the store
on my way home and get so--
Nice.
[ACCELERATOR]
Awesome light show!
Picked up a new technique huh?
[ACCELERATOR] Controlling
the iron sand using magnetism.
I have to admit,
it's an interesting idea.
[MIKOTO] What? No way!
But unfortunately, once
you know how it's done,
it's no big deal anymore.
[MIKOTO] I threw
all that at him...
and he doesn't
even have a scratch?
What the...?
[screams]
Huh? That's a lot
of power. Are you...?
[MIKOTO] That's... impossible.
How could I not
know about an esper
who can shrug off
my attacks like that?
Ah, I understand now!
I was wondering what this was
since it wasn't on the schedule.
You... You're the Original.
[ACCELERATOR]
The clones are supposed
to take the Original's place.
But if I fight you...
that would considerably
reduce the number of
lame combat scenarios
I have to go through, right?
I'm really starting
to get tired of doing this...
What do you say? Original...
Tell me why...
Why are you going
along with this project?
Uh... Can we just fight ?
[MIKOTO] Answer me!
You've got some serious power...
There's no way that they
could force you to do anything!
So, what's your reason
for participating
in this insanity?
What could she have
done to deserve this?
Reason. What's my reason?
That's easy...
[ACCELERATOR] My goal is
to acquire absolute power.
[ACCELERATOR]
Not the power
of a Level 5, or
Academy City's top dog.
Nothing that insignificant.
[ACCELERATOR] I'm talking
about the kind of power
that will stop people
from even thinking
about challenging me.
I want invincibility.
You get that, right?
Being a Level 5.
[MIKOTO]
You're nuts... aren't you?
So you want to be invincible...
Is that your excuse?
Seriously?
Power's not enough.
You need absolute power?
[MIKOTO] That's the
reason you're giving me?
The reason you
agreed to kill her?
[ACCELERATOR]
You make it sound so dirty.
Stop talking like
I'm a murderer...
I'm fighting things
not real people.
They're manufactured
with the push of a button.
What are you so
worked up about?
Oh, I get it now.
I stole your thunder, huh?
That move was your ace in the
hole, and I just annihilated it.
Oh, wow...
Man, I knew you were
ranked lower than me,
but I still thought
you'd have more
to bring to the table
than a little electricity.
[ACCELERATOR] All right...
Now it's my turn to play...
You're in pretty
rough shape, though,
so I'm not expecting too much.
But at least try to keep
me entertained, okay?
Third-string.
[MISAKA 6-A] One moment, please.
[MISAKA 6-A] "Combat
outside of the project may
introduce errors into the
computational predictions. So,"
says Misaka,
"this should stop now."
[MISAKA 6-B] "Especially
since Big Sister is a Level 5.
[MISAKA 6-C] The skew from such
combat would be considerable.
[MISAKA 6-D] Rather than
shortening the scheduled time...
[MISAKA 6-E]
the very project itself...
[MISAKA 6-F] would be
at risk of being ruined.
[MISAKA 6-G]
Further, Misaka has,
[MISAKA 6-H] in anticipation
of experiments yet to come,
[MISAKA 6-I] received
specific programming...
[MISAKA 6-J]
and any alterations
to the project would
be very difficult,"
[MISAKA 6-A]
explains Misaka simply.
[ACCELERATOR]
Tch... yeah, yeah, all right.
I get it... I was just
messing around, anyway...
And stop talking
like that. It's creepy.
[ACCELERATOR]
My bad...
I guess I never
introduced myself, did I?
[MIKOTO] Not satisfied
with being the strongest...
You probably
figured it out by now,
but I'm the one looking
after your clones...
They're helping me
achieve invincibility.
[MIKOTO]
...a Level 5 who wants
to become something
even greater...
There's no doubt...
This boy is...
[ACCELERATOR] I should
be grateful to you, really.
[MIKOTO] ...the
controller of vectors...
the first-ranked esper
in Academy City.
Hello there, I'm Accelerator.
It's a pleasure.
[MISAKA 6-A] Numbers
nine-nine-nine-five
through one-zero-zero-zero-seven
clear the rails.
[MISAKA 6-B]
One-zero-zero-zero-eight--
[MIKOTO]
What's wrong with you?
[MIKOTO] It's so screwed up...
Why are you going
along with this project?
You're going to be killed...
I don't get it...
Why would you do this?
[MIKOTO] Why?
You're breathing, aren't you?
You have life, don't you?
Isn't that enough?
[MIKOTO] Who are you?
[MIKOTO] Just who
the hell are you?
What, not who...
Misaka is a product
created for this project...
Artificial bodies...
with artificial minds...
Laboratory animals,
with a unit price
of one hundred
and eighty thousand.
[MISAKA 6-A]
Goodbye then... Big Sister.
[KUROKO] Y-Yeah...
that's why I called.
She hasn't come
back to the dorm yet,
so, I thought to myself,
"Maybe she's at Saten's."
Is she?
She hasn't stopped
by here at all...
Have you tried Uiharu?
Maybe she's there.
[KUROKO] I heard
from Uiharu earlier...
Uh, I mean...
Yes, of course...
If she isn't at your
place or here, then...
Listen, Shirai...
I'm just going to
throw this out there...
She could have a
boyfriend. It's possi--
No she couldn't!
There's absolutely no way!
I'm disappointed
in you, Saten!
Sissy would never do
anything so improper!
She belongs to me!
To me, alone, do you understand?
Hey, I was only kidding!
Calm down. Uh, hello?
Are you still there?
[SATEN] Geez. I wonder
what that was about.
[DOCTOR 2-A] It's the
simplest thing in the world.
All you have to do is
give us your DNA map, okay?
[MIKOTO]
Don't do it!
They're not going to use
your DNA map to cure
muscular dystrophy!
They're going to use it
to make clones of you!
It'll be the basis for a
horrible experiment!
Say no!
[MIKOTO] No, wait!
Listen to me!
Please, just liste--
[MISAKA 6-K]
So that's it...
You were the cause
of all this, Big Sister.
[MISAKA 6-L] The reason
Misaka was made...
[MISAKA 6-M] The reason
Misaka is killed...
[MISAKA 6-N] All of it.
[MISAKA 6-K] Everything.
[MIKOTO] Oh, wow...
I've been here all night.
[NUNOTABA] Long time no see.
[NUNOTABA] I thought I spotted
a delinquent camping out
all night on this bench.
I know why you're here...
You found out about
the project, didn't you?
[NUNOTABA] There's no way
you can put a stop to it.
That's why I told you
not to get involved.
[MIKOTO] No, you didn't.
Oh, dear...
Is that right? My mistake.
[MIKOTO] It's wrong.
[MIKOTO] How can they
get away with this?
I don't know anything about
Level 6 or whatever...
but is it something they want
so badly they'll kill so many?
Everyone involved
with the experiment
must be completely insane.
[NUNOTABA]
It's not quite like that.
I won't deny that
there's something crazy
about it all, but if we're
talking about right and wrong,
that's another matter.
Suppose there was a way
to develop a miracle drug
that could cure cancer...
but doing so would
require experimental data
from twenty thousand
guinea pigs.
What would you do?
You would say
"we have no other choice."
[MIKOTO] That's
different though.
[NUNOTABA] Is it?
They're both alive.
[NUNOTABA] And, from a
researchers perspective,
they are essentially
the same thing.
The Sisters are
artificially produced
guinea pigs, made for the
sake of reaching Level 6...
Of course...
There are those who are in it
for their own personal gain...
and there are a few of them who
really do have a screw loose...
But across the board,
none of them recognize
this as being murder.
[NUNOTABA]
And neither, in fact, did I.
[MIKOTO] Wasn't that the
reason you were spreading
those money cards
around the city?
To interfere with
the experiments?
[NUNOTABA]
That's correct.
[MIKOTO] But why?
They're not even human...
Why would you want
to protect them? Why?
[NUNOTABA] As you know,
Project Radio Noise was designed
in order to mass
produce Level 5 espers...
When it was frozen, I left the
project team... but then...
When the Sisters were taken
over by Project Level 6 Shift...
I was called in once again.
[NUNOTABA] We started
some in-house experiments
and found there were
no particular problems
with their individual minds.
The Misaka Net
is in good shape.
It looks problem-free.
[NUNOTABA] Want some?
I'd prefer that to
having you stare at me.
[MISAKA 6-O] What is this?
[NUNOTABA] A cup of tea.
It should be included in
the data input by Testament.
Misaka's first cup of tea.
[MISAKA 6-O]
"It is somewhat different
than the information
in the Testament data,"
Misaka says curiously...
"In addition to the
flavor of the tea leaves,
there is a subtle sweetness
and fullness to the-- "
[NUNOTABA] Oh, well that would
be because it's milk tea.
Basically, tea with milk added
to it... It's my favorite.
[MISAKA 6-O] Milk tea...
[NUNOTABA] It's been a long
time since we've met like this.
Even so... you really
haven't changed much.
You're just like
the first "you."
[NUNOTABA] Eight thousand
nine hundred and eleven units
have been consumed so far
in in-house experiments...
In that time your
emotional aspects
haven't developed at all...
However, your memories
and experiences,
in pure data form,
have all been gathered
together and shared...
Which is done via
the Misaka Network.
And that means the next unit
will know the
flavor of milk tea...
It's a truly fantastic system,
the Misaka Network.
"Testament plays a
very significant role,
as well, right?"
Misaka asks, to clarify...
"It is through Testament that
the Misakas are programmed.
That's how they learn
to conceptualize feelings
and remember them as data."
"As a result of this process...
the Misakas are readily able
to face the experiments,"
says Misaka,
expressing gratitude.
[NUNOTABA] It's time now.
[NUNOTABA] You're heading
out for external training...
Do you have anything
to ask before you go?
[MISAKA 6-O]
What is the air outside like?
Is it sweet? Or, perhaps, spicy?
[MISAKA 6-O] "I was told the
air outside is delicious,
so I'm curious...
Misaka has a preference for
things that are sweet, you see,"
explains Misaka shyly,
revealing her tastes.
Well... you'll find out
for yourself soon enough.
[NUNOTABA] The glare from the
sun is pretty strong today.
[NUNOTABA]
Pretty disappointing isn't it?
[MISAKA 6-O]
No. Not disappointing at all.
A number of aromas
are stimulating
my nasal cavities...
and slowly filling up my chest.
[MISAKA 6-O] An irregular
breeze blows through my hair,
sweeping past my body
like a gentle touch.
Light rays from the
sun beam down on my skin...
and I can feel my cheeks
taking in their heat.
[MISAKA 6-O]
The outside world...
it really is a
dazzling place, isn't it?
[NUNOTABA] I hate to sound
trite, but it was that simple.
Something changed
in that moment.
From then on, I could no longer
think of them as products.
Because she seemed so
much more human than me...
She saw the beauty
in the world...
and I could only ever see
it as a warped, ugly thing.
[NUNOTABA] What about you?
What do you think of them?
[MIKOTO] I'm not sure.
It's difficult to think
of clones as human...
and why should I help them
when they seem so ready
to accept their own deaths?
[MIKOTO] However,
there are still the people
who took my DNA map
and used it for
their sick experiment.
[MIKOTO]
Them I intend to deal with.
[UIHARU]
Yeah, that's what happened...
She called me up
out of the blue,
asked me about some kind of
code, and then she just--
Wait a minute.
You don't know
what's going on, either?
[KUROKO] Where are you, Sissy?
[KUROKO] Finally!
Where've you been, you
could have at least called me!
[KUROKO]
Your clothes are all torn up...
What happened to you?
[MIKOTO] Oh... well, you know...
Same thing as usual...
I'm gonna go take a shower.
[KUROKO] Um...
[KUROKO]
Hold on a second!
[ringing phone]
Hello?!
Uiharu?
Oh... yes, just n--
I mean, late last night...
That's right... There's
nothing to worry about...
Please pass the message on
to Haru'ue... Okay, bye.
[ringing phone]
[KUROKO] Hello? Oh, Saten...
Yes, late last night...
I told you, you had
it wrong, did I not?
Yes... it's all fine.
There's no need to worry
about anything... Right.
[MIKOTO] Listen, Kuroko.
Do you have a minute?
[MIKOTO] I'm so sorry
I had all of you worried.
[MIKOTO] This is
my way of apologizing...
It's my treat,
so go ahead, enjoy!
[HARU'UE] This is incredible.
[SATEN] So, spill, Misaka.
Where were you?
What were you up to?
[MIKOTO] I wanted to do...
some stargazing.
--[SATEN] Um, Stargazing?
--[UIHARU] Stargazing?
[MIKOTO] Yep... that's right.
[MIKOTO] Well, you know...
Like every now and again,
when you get into a
schmaltzy kind of mood.
[MIKOTO]
And you just want to sit
on the swings in the park,
swaying back and forth,
humming cheesy songs to yourself
and staring at the stars...
You get it.
No, I don't...
I don't even know what
"schmaltzy" means.
Oh you don't, huh?
Well, it's just how
I was feeling last night.
I meant to ask:
Did you ever figure out what
that code was for yesterday?
What do you mean?
Oh, it was just...
[MIKOTO] A-Ah... the code!
Well that was... it was...
[KUROKO] What is it, Sissy?
[UIHARU] Are you okay?
[SATEN] Please, Misaka,
is something wrong?
[MIKOTO] I can see you.
[MIKOTO] All of you...
I can see you there beside me...
but I can't... I can't...
What are you saying?
[SATEN] The arcade!
Let's go to the arcade, Misaka!
It's been a long time...
and I want to take on
the punching machine again.
Great idea! The arcade!
[HARU'UE] Oh... in that case,
I want to do one of these again.
[KUROKO] Oh, yeah, I remember.
[UIHARU] We'll do that, too!
[SATEN] Let's go, let's go!
We need to clear our heads.
[MIKOTO] You guys...
Just one thing...
I want you to
remember this, Misaka.
[SATEN] No matter what,
we're always here for you.
If your burden is ever too
heavy, just say the word, okay?
[MIKOTO] Mmm.
[UIHARU] It really has been
a long time, hasn't it?
[SATEN] A long, long time!
[HARU'UE] I wonder if
the moles are still there.
[KUROKO] I'll show you the
technique I have for that game.
[MIKOTO] Yes. I can see now.
[KUROKO] I'm takin'
you down, just wait!
[MIKOTO] All the more reason...
[MIKOTO] However,
there are still the people
who took my DNA map and used
it for their sick experiment...
Them I intend to deal with.
[NUNOTABA] Well, aren't
you a defiant one ?
[NUNOTABA]
It isn't just one facility...
There are more than twenty.
Are you planning
to do this alone?
[MIKOTO] Yes, I am... No one
else needs to get involved.
[MIKOTO] I'm the one
who made this mess.
I will be the one...
...to clean it up.
[SATEN] Ugh... I'm still
worried about Misaka.
[UIHARU]
So am I.
[KUROKO] Time for a snack!
[UIHARU] Shirai?
[KUROKO] It's Anshindo's
special, magical,
limited-time-only summer buns!