[sobbing]
I'm home, Mikoto.
What's the matter, dear?
Why are you crying?
Oh, a boo-boo!
Now, now, it'll be all right.
[YOUNG MIKOTO] Really?
You just be a good girl,
and it will be fixed up,
as good as new.
How's that gonna happen...?
Ooh, I know!
Is Santa gonna come
and make it all better?
[MISAKA'S MOM] Heh,
heh, heh. Santa...?
In the middle of spring?
Yep... that's right...
The old fellow is a friend of
mine, so I'll see what I can do.
You know Santa?!
Sure!
Now, close those eyes
and get some sleep, okay?
[MISAKA'S MOM] There...
breakfast is served.
[YOUNG MIKOTO] Mama!
[YOUNG MIKOTO laughs]
Look, Mama! All better...!
See...? Just like you told me!
That's right...
[MIKOTO] Life was so much
simpler as a child...
Whenever something went wrong,
Mama would fix it while I slept.
Like magic.
If only the
experiment...
and everything
that's happened...
could just be a bad dream...
Something that vanished...
evaporated when
I opened my eyes.
Isn't it a beautiful
morning, Sissy?!
[KUROKO] Oh, I just want
a moment to savor this
before getting punched.
Hey... Good morning.
[MIKOTO] It is a nice day today.
[MIKOTO] But I haven't
been dreaming.
Mama isn't here now to make
every little problem go away.
Santa stopped making house
calls a long time ago.
[KUROKO hums]
[MIKOTO] And no hero is going to
come dashing to
the rescue, either.
[KUROKO] Are you
going out again today?
[MIKOTO] Yeah.
Just once more.
Then it should all be over.
Huh?
[MIKOTO] Today...
[MIKOTO] Today is the day...
I'm ending this.
[MIKOTO] It's almost time now.
Sorry, guys.
Maybe someday
you'll forgive me...
Maybe someday you'll understand.
[MIKOTO] Tree Diagram...
The greatest supercomputer
in the world.
Loaded aboard the
satellite Orihime I
and launched into
space by Academy City
under the pretense that it would
be analyzing climate data.
Every few weeks, it
projects the movement
of all the particles in
the Earth's atmosphere,
predicting the weather for
the entire month in one go...
The rest of the time,
it performs calculations
for all sorts of Academy
City-based research projects.
Also...
It is the simulator that's
directing the creation
and slaughter of twenty
thousand clones.
[KAMIJO] Hey.
Remedial lessons
for you too, huh...?
What class did you fail, Zapper?
Oh, hey...
It's you again.
My name's Mikoto
Misaka, not Zapper.
I'm really tired, and
there are some things
I need to save my
strength for today...
So I'm just going to skip
the part where I zap you.
Oh, so you can say
"zap," but I can't?
Never mind...
Your sister's not
with you today?
I just wanted to thank
her for helping me
carry all those drinks
home yesterday.
Hold on...!
You mean you saw her again?
Uh, yeah... I saw her.
What for?
What do you mean,
"what for?"...
I just ran into her, that's all.
Sun again tomorrow!
[MIKOTO] Stupid things...
I really can't
stand those blimps.
[KAMIJO] Huh?
What's wrong with them?
[MIKOTO] They're nothing
but big computers.
Programmed to control us.
For now.
But Tree Diagram's
reign is about to end...
I'm destroying that machine.
[KAMIJO] Uh...? Hey!
[MIKOTO] Today!
[KAMIJO] What is the
deal with that girl...?
I mean, jeez!
Is she always
so high-strung?
[KAMIJO] Eh?
Hey, Zapper.
You were just over
there, weren't you?
[MISAKA 10032] "Since Misaka's
name is obviously not Zapper...
I can only assume that you
are referring to the cat,"
Misaka tells the rude boy.
Oh, sorry. You're
the sister, huh...?
Without the goggles, there's
no way to tell you two apart.
Oh, by the way...
thank you for yesterday.
[MISAKA 10032] "Your words
of gratitude are noted,
but they were not my objective,"
replies Misaka honestly.
"I removed the goggles because
I needed to feed the cat,
and previous experience
has taught me that
they are disturbed by reflective
surfaces, such as lenses,"...
Misaka explains
her wardrobe change.
Yeah, cats are like that...
So... Why put them
back on, then?
"Because it was
no longer necessary
to have them off. See?"
asks Misaka patiently.
Okay...
so you fed him already?
No, I haven't fed him.
Uh...
then why did you put
the goggles back on?
Well?
[MISAKA 10032 "The reason behind
that action is unimportant,"
Misaka says,
refusing to explain.
Huh?
Ah, I get it...
You didn't want anybody seeing
your sweet side, did you?
[MISAKA 10032] No.
It is not that, exactly.
Fine, I give. What is it?
Hello!
[MISAKA 10032]
"I refuse to answer that,"
Misaka states, making
herself quite clear.
[KAMIJO sighs]
Well... all right,
if you say so.
See you later.
"Hold on a moment,"
Misaka says, instructing
you to stop walking.
Just tell me what
the deal is, will ya?
"You were going to leave...
You were going to
abandon this creature.
Walking away from a
helpless, hungry cat.
How can you bring yourself
to do something so cruel...?
Well?"... Misaka asks sternly.
What's with you?
I'm not abandoning him.
You've got food!
"Misaka does have food,
but feeding the cat
is nonetheless
impossible for her,"
Misaka says, finally relenting.
"Misaka has a
critical defect
that prevents her from
interacting with the cat,"
Misaka explains further.
A defect...?
I'm sure it can't be that bad.
"The descriptor
is appropriate...
It's Misaka's body...
It constantly emits a
weak magnetic field,"...
Misaka says,
explaining her defect.
It is not strong enough
for people to detect,
but animals are
highly sensitive to it.
Okay, so... let me
see if I understand.
Animals tend not to like you
because you're a walking magnet?
[MISAKA 10032] "It is not
that they do not like me.
They simply find it difficult
to be around me,"...
Misaka says, correcting
your previous statement.
Then give me the food...
I wouldn't mind feeding the ca--
"That is not enough...
Do you not wish to take him
in and give him a home?"...
Misaka pointedly inquires.
"If you do not know what
happens to animals taken in
by the Health Department,
I am happy to inform you.
Well,"... says Misaka, beginning
her illustrative tale...
First, the unfortunate
creature is placed inside
a polycarbonate case...
Then, twenty milliliters of a
chemical called ASD-10 are inj-
Stop talking!
That is seriously
disturbing information...
If you feel so bad,
why don't you adopt him.
"Unfortunately, it
would not be possible
for Misaka to raise a cat,"
Misaka answers honestly.
"In addition to the
aforementioned critical defect,
Misaka's living space is
somewhat unconventional
and thus not conducive
to pet ownership,"...
Misaka clearly
states her reasons.
Still, I...
Uh...
Okay, okay.
[meows]
I guess you're
coming with me.
[meows]
[KUSAKABE] You say there's a
strange pain in your chest, huh?
[KUSAKABE] I don't see anything
that's out of the ordinary.
[AMAMI] But Number 10031's
turn is coming up tomorrow.
We don't want anything
impeding the experiment, do we?
[KUSAKABE] Yeah, you're right...
We should probably
look a bit harder.
[MISAKA 10031]
"No.
It is not something that
will affect the experiment,"
says Misaka, offering
her own analysis.
Well... since the tests aren't
actually showing anything,
your word is
good enough for me.
Sorry...
"Suppose you were to encounter
a clone of yourself...
What would that experience
be like for you?
How would you... feel?"
Misaka wishes to know.
A clone of myself...?!
Ugh, I don't think
I'd like that at all!
Oh, really...?
But it could be useful.
[AMAMI] What...?!
Imagine for a second
a living copy of yourself
standing in front of you.
Looking like you and talking
to you in your own voice!
Just thinking about it makes
my insides all squirmy!
[KUSAKABE] Well...
when you put it like that,
it does sound
kind of creepy.
[MIKOTO] I can't take it...
You showing up like this...
Looking like you do!
Just go away, all right?!
That is how
Big Sister feels.
Misaka is creepy.
Someone she wants
nothing to do with.
[FEMALE TOUR GUIDE 12-A]
Hello and welcome
to the Academy City Tour Bus...
We are so glad you chose
to ride with us today!
We are now entering
School District 23,
the area of the city devoted
to space exploration.
In this area,
as the name suggests,
you will find a
variety of facilities
specializing in
space technology,
including the Academy City
Space Exploration Center,
which boasts its own
rocket launch site.
The building you see
on the left-hand side
is the data center for the
most powerful supercomputer
in the world, Tree Diagram...
This center is a hub
for data exchange...
It brings us the city's
weather foreca-
[JANITOR 12-A]
It's unusual for a student
to be dropping by at this hour.
Sorry... I'm writing
a summer break report
and I needed to
do some research.
That's very
studious of you.
Or it would be, anyway...
if you hadn't waited until the
very last minute to get it done.
[MIKOTO laughs]
[JANITOR 12-A]
Word of advice:
This close to sunset
you want to avoid
going anywhere near the fence.
If you do, the security
robots will swarm ya.
Thank you.
I'll be careful.
[MIKOTO] The data center...
The only point of contact
for communications
with Tree Diagram.
From there, I'll hack
in and program it
to produce a false prediction.
Like... "Emergency report:
Have observed a critical error
in the ongoing experiment
titled Project Level 6 Shift."
"The error arose as a
result of the battle between
test subject Accelerator
and Railgun...
The damage done
is irreparable...
Consequently, test
subject Accelerator
will no longer be able
to achieve Level 6."
The researchers, who
have put all their eggs
in Tree Diagram's basket,
will be thrown into a panic.
[MIKOTO] Of course, if they
order a recalculation,
they'll realize that the error
report was inaccurate.
They're bound to catch onto
the trick sooner or later...
However...
before they do, I'll drive the
entire project into bankruptcy.
[PUNK 12-A] Geez.
You could've saved
yourself a lot of pain.
That's my...
Shut up, you moron!
Wait, that's all you have?
Huh?
[cat meows]
[KAMIJO] Hold on.
Black cats are supposedly
bad luck, right?
"Why does he keep
meowing like that?"
asks Misaka,
expressing confusion.
Well, my guess is he's upset
because he's still hungry.
[MISAKA 10032]
So feed him again.
[KAMIJO] How about you
give it a try this time?
I told you... It is
impossible for me to feed--
Oh, come on... try.
[meow]
You see, it worked.
He's eating just fine.
Does he appear
to be upset now?
No way... He looks
pretty happy to me.
[MISAKA 10032]
Are you happy, cat?
[meow]
[KAMIJO chuckles]
Uh, well... you want
to give him a name?
A new name...?
But I thought you
named him Zapper.
Not Zapper...
He's your cat, right?
You should give
him a name you like.
Very well.
It's "Dog."
Huh?
Misaka has chosen a name
for the black cat,
and that name is Dog.
He is a cat called Dog. Heh.
Come on... honestly...
Can't you think of anything
better than that...?
You know, something that's
a little bit more dignified.
"Okay. King Henry VIII,"
Misaka suggests with
a straight face.
Too dignified.
Very well. I will call
him "Schrödinger."
Quit messing around!
Thought experiment or not,
the man talked about
locking a cat in a cage
with some poison and
radioactive material.
Obviously not a cat lover!
All right... I shall
put it on hold for now.
On hold. Yes?
[meow]
I see where
this is going...
Please don't name him
"On Hold," I'm begging you.
Just don't.
[MISAKA 10032] "By the way, what
is your current destination?
This is a different route than
the one we took yesterday
with the beverages,"
Misaka observes accurately.
A little detour...
There's a book that
I need to pick up.
"Do you wish to go to the
shopping district, then?"
Misaka asks and
then points out...
"Geographically speaking,
making a right turn at
the previous intersection
would be the shorter route."
[KAMIJO] Nope... that's not it.
I'm headed for a used
book store past there.
I don't imagine raising a cat
has changed much over the years.
"You are going to the
store to find a book
on how to properly
care for a cat,"
says Misaka,
seeking confirmation.
Yeah, I'd say that
about sums it up.
If it was just me, I'd be fine,
but you were at my place, right?
You saw the nun's habit and
the priestess's robes...?
It's for those two.
"In other words, you intend
to shirk your responsibility
and foist caring for the cat
onto somebody else."...
Misaka says, clarifying.
No, that isn't what
I'm saying at all.
What's wrong...? Are you angry?
"No, I am not angry...
However, if you fail
to treat the cat
with adequate care
and concern...
I will have you charged with
destruction of property,"
states Misaka as
a serious warning.
I knew it. You are angry.
No, I am not angry.
Well, I'm gonna go in
and see what I can find...
You wait out here for me.
"I understand,"...
Misaka acknowledges
the instruction.
There was a hidden
meaning in there, I know it.
Oh... now that I
think about it...
I probably shouldn't go into
the store carrying a cat.
I do not mean to sound as if
I am lecturing you about this,
but please do not give him
to me, as I cannot hold--
[KAMIJO] Here,
catch! Kitty Bomb!
Your magnetic field
freaks him out...
but if you can get
past that barrier,
that'll be a sign of a
real bond between you!
"Horrible boy...
Does he think he can
get away with that...?
One simply does not use a kitten
to play catch." Misaka says,
talking to herself
under her breath.
[meow]
Is that an
upset meow?
[meow]
Or a happy one...?
How do I tell them apart?
[yelling]
We were out of line.
We're sorry man.
We get the message.
You don't need to--
Oh, come on...
You were the ones who started
it in the first place.
You don't really think
you're going to get off
with an apology, do you?
[PUNK 12-B] It hurts!
It hurts...! It hurts!
Please, just stop! Ahh!
[PUNK 12-C yells]
Pathetic...
I know about ten thousand
girls who can take
much worse than that without
so much as a whimper.
No, please!
[ACCELERATOR]
Hey, help a guy out.
I gotta work up an appetite
for dinner somehow.
[ACCELERATOR sighs]
Yeah... I guess it is about
that time again, isn't it?
Lucky you.
It looks like you get to
live for another day.
[MISAKA 10031]
Thank you for waiting.
"I hope I have
not kept you long...
I am Misaka 10031, your next
opponent," Misaka reports.
Tch... okay...
You guys get kinda'
confusing after awhile.
"Should I apologize for your
confusion?" asks Misaka.
[ACCELERATOR] I don't need
an apology from somebody
who'll be dead before tomorrow.
[MISAKA 10032]
Operation confirmed.
Misakas 10031 and
10032 will proceed
with the predetermined
course of action.
[meows]
[MIKOTO] This is strange...
There isn't a hint
of anyone here.
If the sensors
weren't working,
the cameras probably
aren't, either.
[MIKOTO] This facility
is the end-all be-all,
the point of communication
with Academy City's brain.
[MIKOTO] But here I am.
Moving around unimpeded
after getting past
their meager display
of exterior security.
Have they fled...?
Is this a trap?
Whatever the case, there
should be more to it than this.
How do they benefit from
letting me get this far in?
Are they just that sure
that hacking into the
system is impossible?
Even the control
room is deserted.
The facility appears
to be functioning...
But...
This didn't
just happen...
The utter emptiness, the layer
of dust coating everything.
This place has been
abandoned for awhile.
But why?
This is nothing like
what I expected.
I'll do what I came here
for and--Is this it?
What does that mean?
Number of transmissions
today: 0...?
There should be several
hundred requests
to Tree Diagram each day.
No... the requests are here.
They just haven't
been processed...
Nor were yesterday's,
or the day before...
[MIKOTO] These are reports.
A bunch of them ...
23rd Report... 24th Report...
What does that say?!
"This is the final
report regarding
the disappearance
of Tree Diagram."
"On June 28 at zero
zero twenty hours,
all communications
ceased and Tree Diagram
disappeared from
its satellite track.
That same day,
at zero one fifteen,
Search Party 1 was dispatched."
"Later, at zero three forty,
one section of Tree Diagram's
remnants was recovered...
Analysis indicates that
Tree Diagram was...
Tree Diagram...
...no longer exists.
Then...
[KAMIJO] Let's see here...
Cat book...
cat book... cat book...
[meows]
[MIKOTO] Tree Diagram
doesn't exist.
[MISAKA 10031]
The experiments continue.
[MIKOTO] There must be something
I can do to save them!
[MISAKA 10031] "Misaka must go
on to the next experiment,"
says Misaka.
[MIKOTO] Stop...! Please!