[KAMIJO] Come on!
What is with
this thing?
[MIKOTO] Is that...
[THUG S1 4-A] We got
ourselves a cutie here...
Oooh... and she's
from Tokiwadai, too.
[THUG S1 4-B] Wanna come with
us; have some fun tonight?
[THUG S1 4-C] We'll even
take you back to your dorm...
Of course, there's no telling
how late it might be by then.
[THUGS laugh]
[MIKOTO] What do
these idiots think
they're going to accomplish
by talking to me?
Pathetic.
Everyone else is
pretending not to see.
It's not that they don't care.
They just can't do
anything about it.
If they interfered, they'd
only get themselves hurt.
And that wouldn't help anyone.
Everyone has to look
out for themselves...
That's the way it works.
And if there is somebody
out there who would
jump in the middle of this
to help out a stranger...
Well, that person
is just a fool.
[KAMIJO] Oh, hey, there you are!
Thanks for keeping
her company, guys!
You shouldn't wander
off like that.
You know how much I worry!
I gave it
plenty of money.
I don't understand...!
Is it out of order?
Seriously?!
Heh.
[KAMIJO] Please don't
screw with me today...
Give me back my money!
[MIKOTO] Are you done yet?
You just going to stand
there like an idiot...?
Are you gonna buy
something or not?
What...? Hold on...
[MIKOTO] I seriously
need to rehydrate.
If I don't get a drink, I could
pass out at any given moment.
You're one rude chick.
[MIKOTO] When will you get it
through your thick skull?
My name is Mikoto Misaka!
Is it really that hard
for you to remember?!
Great.
So I guess that hasn't
changed either, huh...?
Why is it that my shocks
have no effect on you?
[KAMIJO] I don't know!
But it serves you right for
using your ability like that!
[MIKOTO] Well...
if you're done, I'm going
to get what I came for.
I've got some serious business
with this vending machine.
[KAMIJO] Uh...
about this machine...
It has a tendency
to eat your money.
Not five minutes ago, it took
mine and gave me nothing.
So, you
got yoinked?
Well, what was
the damage...?
How much did
it take you for?
2000.
Wow! 2000?!
You gave it that big of a bill?
[MIKOTO laughs]
Then of course it ate
your money, you idiot!
I can't tell you how
much I needed a laugh...
So... I'll get you
your money's worth.
[KAMIJO] Eh?
Yeah...
This machine and I go way back.
You wouldn't believe
how much money I--
[KAMIJO] Hmm?
[MIKOTO] Uh, never mind...
Anyway, like I said,
I'm going to make this thing
give you what you paid for.
Uh, you know...
I don't have a good
feeling about this.
Just forget it.
[MIKOTO] Hah!
[CLERK 11-A]
Thank you for waiting.
[SATEN] No problem.
[UIHARU] So, that's it?
She's back to normal,
just like that?
Uh-huh.
And just when I had
decided to leave her alone
and wait for her
to confide in me.
There's no reason for Sissy
to know how worried I've been.
All that would do is
make her worry, instead.
[KUROKO sighs]
I just hope we never have
to go through that again.
[SATEN] Hmm...
Let's recap: she went out last
night without eating anything...
She didn't give us
any details about
where she was going or
what she was doing...
It fits.
I'm sure now. There can
only be one explanation...
There's a boy involved...
There must be.
I wonder who it is.
Oh...! W-W-Wow!
Absolutely not!
There's no boy!
That's why she's been acting
so strangely because--
That's right. Because
she's lovestruck.
It all makes
sense now...!
Why she was
sneaking around.
Why she couldn't turn
to any of us for advice.
Why she kept it all
completely secret...
[SATEN] I know!
[UIHARU] I wonder what type
of boy Misaka would choose.
I'll bet he's a
gallant young gentleman
and as handsome
as a prince, too!
Well, handsome is
always a plus...
but I think Misaka would
also want to go out with a guy
who was intelligent
and interesting.
[UIHARU gasps]
Wait...! She stays
out all night
and doesn't come home
until morning...
You don't think she could be...
[SATEN] Are you okay, Uiharu?
[KUROKO] No... there's no way...
Of all people, Sissy wouldn't...
[alarm sounds]
An alarm?
What the... you
guys are really quick.
[UIHARU] Just listen...
That sounds like an alarm from
a vending machine, right...?
Well, what do you think?
[KUROKO] A vending machine
in that direction...?
Could it be...?
So, what should
we do, Shirai?
I'm gonna go see what
might've set it off.
Well then,
I'll come, too.
That's okay If I need
backup, I'll contact you.
Hold on!
[MIKOTO] Wait up...!
What are you so scared of?
I can't... run any farther...
[MIKOTO] Honestly!
You could at least help
me carry all this stuff!
I did my part.
I made that machine cough up
everything it owed you.
Well, I didn't
want to steal any--
[MIKOTO] Technically, they
already belong to you.
If I accept this,
I'm not a bystander,
but an accomplice.
[MIKOTO] Here.
There's more where
that came from.
[KAMIJO] Whoa!
Hold on! Hold on...! Ow...!
There are some hot
ones in there, too!
[MIKOTO] It's not my fault.
I can't choose what kind of
drink it spits out, you know.
What's with
you, anyway?
The littlest thing is enough
to send you running...
It doesn't help my pride
that the guy who beat me
is a big crybaby!
[KAMIJO] Huh?
What did you say?
Please! Don't act like
you don't remember.
You managed to defeat me, both
in town and out by the riverbed.
Wait, so I've been
getting into fights
with a middle-school girl?
Really?
You're actually trying to
pretend that you've forgotten?
How pathetic can you be?
[KAMIJO] What have I been doing?
Whatever,
just drink...
You should
be thankful.
I can think of at least
one girl who would swoon
to get a present
from me.
Aw, gimme a break.
This isn't some manga...
Girls don't actually "swoon."
Heh... if only that were true.
Of course, you probably
don't know what they call me
at Tokiwadai Middle
School, do you?
[KUROKO] Hi, Sissyyyyy!
I heard a vending machine
alarm, so I came running.
And sure enough, here you are!
[MIKOTO] Here we go.
Speak of the devil...
[KAMIJO] What's up?
[MIKOTO] Uh,
something wrong, Kuro--
Geez! What's the
matter with you?
I thought she was wrong...
but it's true...!
How awful!
You're having a secret
assignation with a boy!
[MIKOTO] Hold on a minute!
It's a pleasure to meet
you, gentleman caller.
Whoa,
what now?
The name's Kuroko Shirai,
and I have the honor of being
Mikoto's right hand gal.
Her one and only
partner. Forever.
As you appear to be an
acquaintance of Sissy's,
I am bound by social etiquette
to at least introduce
myself to you.
Uh... okay...
[KUROKO] Are you kidding me?
He's not exactly what you
would call "impressive."
Could someone like him
really be with Sissy?
My, it doesn't take very much
to incapacitate him, does it?
I thought you would have
had better taste than this.
[MIKOTO] Excuse me?
Do you seriously think a
blithering idiot like this
is my boyfriend?
How stupid can you be?!
[KAMIJO] Wait! Your what?!
[KUROKO] No, of
course I didn't...!
I thought it seemed
like a strange pairing.
[MIKOTO] Come on!
Get back down here!
[KUROKO] Let me think.
Of course, I would love
for you to wash your hands
of this troglodyte
and allow me to escort you
back home to our room, but...
it might be best for you
to build up some immunity
to the charms of men so you are
not led further astray later on.
And, really...
I don't think I have
anything to fear from this
helpless, goofy little monkey...
In fact, it's possible that
he's so pathetic that you will
become disillusioned
with men in general,
and then I will be
there to console you!
[KUROKO laughs]
[KUROKO] And, besides...
You finally seem
like yourself again.
[MIKOTO] I said,
are you listening?!
[KUROKO] I have nothing
more to say...
and, as I have some things to
attend to, I will take my leave.
I'm sure I can trust you not to
embarrass yourself
here, Sissy...
[MIKOTO] Hey...!
--So Good-bye.
--What do you mean by that?!
[KAMIJO] She vanished!
[MIKOTO] Saying something like
that, and then running away!
So there are people in real life
who use the term "Sissy"...
I had no idea...
You Tokiwadai girls
are something else.
She's actually sort
of a special case.
Oh... Is she?
[MIKOTO] Oh, man!
Why am I here?
I need some rest.
[MISAKA 10031] Big Sister?
[KAMIJO] She's back--
Wait... what the...?
You mean...
There's another Zapper?
[MISAKA 10031] "Our appearances
are, indeed, similar.
Which makes sense, as we
are entirely identical
on a genetic level."
Offers Misaka in reply.
[KAMIJO] Huh?
A genetic level...?
Oh, ah! So you
guys're twins, huh?
Moments ago...
I identified a power
identical to Misaka's
being used in the area.
When I arrived, I found
a broken vending machine.
And now I see you with
all of these beverages.
Big Sister, I hope I
am wrong in suspecting
that you are an
accomplice to theft.
[KAMIJO] Hey...!
Your sister is
the perpetrator!
I'm an innocent bystander!
Misaka investigated...
I checked for fingerprints
using my ability.
The results showed that the most
recent set belonged to you.
No way! You can actually tell?
Kidding.
Not laughing...!
Give me a break...!
This sister of yours
could stand to learn...
Uh...
[MIKOTO] Why...?
Of all places...
[MIKOTO] What are you doing
wandering around out here?
[MISAKA 10031] I am
here for training.
But--
What are you
training for...?
Are you joining
Judgment or something?
[MIKOTO] Judgment?
Oh, yeah...
that's what this is.
Come on. Let's talk.
Unfortunately, Misaka
has a schedule to keep.
[MIKOTO] It's okay!
Come with me.
[KAMIJO] Well, every
family is different...
Some more than others...
[MISAKA 10031] Big Sister...
how far are we going to walk?
Misaka's schedule is already
off by thirty-eight seconds.
She must go soon.
The experiment...
The project was shut
down, wasn't it...?
So why...?
[MISAKA 10031] "To which
project are you referring?
Could you be inquiring about
Project Level 6 Shift...?
If so, it is proceeding
on schedule,"...
Misaka says to clarify.
But it's not...!
Still?
[MISAKA 10031] Mm. Yes...
That is correct...
Experiment Number 10020
was just conducted.
[MIKOTO] That's ten...
...thousand?
What is she saying...?
No... They can't...
I thought they went bankrupt!
I read it, but
I don't understand...!
How could they...?
It isn't over yet!
They're still...
killing those girls!
No... that's not true.
It was me... I killed them.
And her, too...
Soon, she'll be...
[MISAKA 10031] Big Sister?
Are you all--
[cat meows]
[MIKOTO] Aww! How adorable!
[MISAKA 10031] "Misaka
found the cute animal,"
says Misaka, trumpeting
her achievement.
[MIKOTO] What do I do now...?
What more...
can I possibly do?
[MISAKA 10031] Big Sister...
Big Sister, it's
a kitty-kiddy.
[MISAKAS] Big Sister...
Big Sister... Big Sister...
[MIKOTO] No, stop it!
Please, stop it!
I can't take it...
You showing up like this...
Looking like you do!
Just go away, all right?!
Okay.
Misaka will leave now.
[thud]
It keeps getting worse.
[KAMIJO] Man.
These are heavy...!
I wonder what was up with
Zapper and her sister...
That was strange.
Wha...!
Aww man, that's
gonna leave a bruise.
[MISAKA 10032]
"You've fallen.
Do you need a hand getting up?"
Misaka asks, offering her help,
somewhat reluctantly.
Thanks a lot, Zapper.
Oh, you aren't her.
You're the sister.
Wait... I thought
you guys wandered off
for a heart-to-heart
or something.
[MISAKA 10032] "Misaka was there
before, and now she is here,"
says Misaka, pointing.
"After we gather them,
where would you like to take
these canned beverages?"...
Asks Misaka,
cleaning up your mess.
Oh, uh, don't
worry about it!
Really, I can
carry them myself...
"After we have
picked them up,
where should we take
these beverages?"
Misaka asks,
repeating the question.
[door opens]
Hello.
Is something the matter...?
You look awfully
flushed, Dr. Amai...
Are you all right?
[AMAI] Don't "Hello" me...!
How could you involve
so many facilities?!
We're supposed to be taking
the lead on Level 6 Shift!
If you scatter the
work around like this,
the patent will never be--
[FOREIGNER 7-A] Now, now,
let's calm down.
We could divide it up
even more than this,
and there would still
be plenty of profit.
You can't possibly
know that!
Oh, but I can.
Listen...
Right now, what's most important
is completing the experiments.
A total of a hundred and
eighty-three facilities
are receiving transfers.
Quite a lot.
If that breaks our mysterious
attacker's sprit, then good...
And should the attacks
continue, well...
The more of those facilities
that are destroyed...
the greater our share of the
profit becomes, doesn't it?
There're so many...
one-hundred-eighty-three...
[MIKOTO] How could it
have been spread between
that many facilities
in such a short time...?
How could one firm possibly
operate on this high a level?
[MIKOTO] Oh, wow...
I'm an idiot...
I can't believe I
didn't see it sooner.
Academy City is under satellite
and camera surveillance
twenty-four hours a day...
There's no way that the city's
senior management could have
failed to notice these
twisted experiments
when they were being held
over and over again outside.
In other words...
All of Academy City...
...is my enemy.
[chewing sounds]
[ACCELERATOR] Ugh...
No flavor left in that piece.
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A]
Hello. Have a sec?
[ACCELERATOR] So, which
lab's errand boy are you?
What makes you think
I'm with a lab?
Only two types of people
ever come near me...
There are the ones who want to
use me for scientific analysis.
And then there are the
idiots who want to fight me
so they can claim the title
of Academy City's top dog.
Hmm... that's very interesting.
[ACCELERATOR] Though, as both
types tend to be full of crap,
I don't see all that much
difference between them.
It's called Level 6 Shift?
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A] Yeah...
An experiment with Tree
Diagram's endorsement.
[ACCELERATOR] Ha!
I'll pass, thanks.
I'm the first-ranked
esper in Academy City...
and that means I'm already
at the top of the heap, buddy.
No one can beat me...
No matter who they
are or what they try,
I'll win every single time.
So why should I
care about becoming
any stronger than I am now?
You're right
about one thing...
You are definitely the
strongest esper in the city.
However...
grand as it is, is that title
gonna be enough for you?
Doesn't it make life
a bit monotonous?
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A]
Just imagine...
If you were to gain
even greater power...
absolute power...
Then what would your
life be like...?
More interesting, I would think.
Even more power
than I already have...
Really?
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A]
I'm glad you decided to come.
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
[ACCELERATOR]
Mass-production of clones,
in violation of
international law.
I gotta admit,
I'm impressed.
You guys are a special
kind of crazy.
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A] Actually,
they were originally intended
for use in a completely
different project...
but things happen...
So all of them wound up
being handed over to us.
Now that you've seen them...
Are you still interested
in achieving Level 6?
[footsteps]
[ACCELERATOR]
Only another nine thousand
nine hundred and seventy
left to go, huh?
What a drag.
[door shuts]
[KUROKO] Okay, Sissy!
The bathtub is all
yours if you want it!
Alright, thank you.
[KUROKO] What happened?
She was in such good
spirits this afternoon.
[KUROKO gasps]
Don't tell me it
was that troglodyte!
[KUROKO demonically]
He shall pay for this!
[MIKOTO] What can I do?
Do I have any moves left...?
Find the mastermind and
put the screws to him...?
No. If Academy City
is green-lighting
these experiments,
that won't do any good...
who would come up with
such a messed-up project
in the first place...?
I get it.
That's why they aren't printing
anything about my attacks!
They don't want to risk
the public finding out
about their illegal
cloning experiments.
But... maybe...
if I were to destroy it...
Academy City would
have nowhere to turn.
If I did that...
My life could never
be normal again.
[MIKOTO chuckles]
What am I thinking...?
They've already killed
ten thousand of me,
and I'm worried about
living a normal life?
[MIKOTO] Hey... Kuroko...
Sissy...? Can I help
you with something?
Supposing--
just supposing...
I did something that
brought calamity and chaos
to Academy City...
What would you do?
Hmm...
If you mean making
off with drinks
from a vending machine
that you damaged,
I guess I would suggest
not doing it again...
That thing is fair game
as far as I'm concerned!
It stole money from me
my first year here!
No, I mean...
If I did something...
something that affected the
very core of Academy City...
[KUROKO] I cannot
pretend to know why
you would even ask a
question like that.
But if someone did something
to threaten the
safety of this city,
I wouldn't hesitate
to take action...
Even if that somebody
was you, Sissy.
[MIKOTO chuckles]
[MIKOTO] Then, despite
all the things you've said,
I suppose our relationship
really does have its limits.
[KUROKO]
No, it doesn't at all...!
Because in a million years,
I know there isn't
even a remote chance
that you would ever
do anything to--
[MIKOTO] Hah...! Gotcha!
I'm just messing with you.
That wasn't nice, Sissy!
[MIKOTO laughs]
[MIKOTO] Thank goodness.
Ooh... come a little
bit closer, Sissy...
[MIKOTO] If I put a
stop to the project
and Kuroko's the
one to catch me...
Well...
That wouldn't be so bad.
[SATEN] I knew it was a boy!
[KUROKO] Absolutely not!
One hundred percent not a boy!
--A boy!
--No it isn't!
--A boy! A boy!
--No it isn't! No it isn't!