- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: A CRIMSON DENIZEN
CALLING HIMSELF LAMIES
APPEARS BEFORE ME AND TELLS ME
SOMETHING DISTURBING.
HE EXPLAINS THAT FRIAGNE
IS ON THE VERGE
OF CARRYING OUT A HORRIFYING
PLAN TO DEVOUR THE ENTIRE CITY.
MY MOTHER, IKE,
YOSHIDA,
EVERYONE WILL SIMPLY VANISH
FROM THE WORLD.
I WAS SHOCKED, BUT I KNEW
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT IN THE MEANTIME,
SHANA WAS BEING FORCED
TO MAKE A DECISION...
ABOUT ME.
- ALASTOR,
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
- Alastor: I SAID WE HAVE
TO DESTROY THE MYSTES.
OVER THE LAST FEW DAYS,
WE'VE BEEN DISTRACTED
BY IT FOR NO GOOD REASON.
- BUT-- BUT WE'RE USING IT
AS BAIT TO FRIAGNE DRAW OUT.
- Alastor: RIGHT NOW HE'S DOING
US MORE HARM THAN GOOD.
- Yuji: MY MOM AND MY FRIENDS
ARE GONNA DISAPPEAR?
- NOT ONLY PEOPLE.
AS THE WORD "DEVOUR" IMPLIES,
HE WILL CONSUME THE ENTIRE CITY
AND CHANGE IT TO POWER
OF EXISTENCE.
- I WON'T LET HIM.
IT'S HORRIBLE.
I WON'T LET HIM DO IT.
- IN THAT CASE,
DO WHAT YOU THINK IS NECESSARY.
- HMM.
- YOSHIDA, I'M SORRY.
SEE YOU AT SCHOOL TOMORROW,
OKAY?
- ( gasps )
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
- BUT SAKAI--
- DON'T TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
HE'S GONE TO DO SOMETHING
THAT ONLY HE
IS UNIQUELY QUALIFIED FOR.
IT MAY NOT AMOUNT TO MUCH IN
THE GREATER SCHEME OF THINGS,
BUT AT LEAST IT WILL PROVE
THAT HE DID HIS BEST
WITH THE TIME HE HAD.
- SHANA--
I HAVE TO LET HER KNOW.
HMM?
- ARE YOU REALLY GOING TO PUT
THE PLAN INTO MOTION, MASTER?
- YES, I AM,
MY ADORABLE MARIANNE.
IT'S UNFORTUNATE,
BUT THAT TORCH-EATING
CORPSE COLLECTOR IS HERE.
THE SITUATION
IS BECOMING SERIOUS.
- BUT YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO START
THE CITY DEVOURING
FOR A WHILE YET.
IF A FLAME HAZE
WERE TO ATTACK IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU'D BE IN GREAT DANGER,
MASTER.
- THERE THERE.
I'M TOUCHED BY YOUR KINDNESS
AND CONCERN, MY DEAR MARIANNE.
BUT NOT TO WORRY, I HAVE
ALREADY TAKEN PRECAUTIONS.
WHEN I BEGIN
THE ACTUAL CITY DEVOURING,
I WILL DIVERT ATTENTION
FROM IT BY ENGAGING IN A BATTLE
WITH THE FLAME-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED LITTLE GIRL.
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
WILL USE THAT AS AN OPPORTUNITY
TO GO AFTER HER OWN PREY,
THE CORPSE COLLECTOR.
ONCE SHE'S OUT OF THE PICTURE,
WE'LL KEEP
THE LITTLE ONE BUSY
AND WAIT FOR TIME TO PASS.
- MMM.
- AS LONG AS I KEEP
RINGING THIS BELL,
THE STRING KEYS
IN ALL OF THE TORCHES
THROUGHOUT THE CITY
WILL BE TIED TOGETHER.
MARIANNE,
WITH THE POWER WE OBTAIN,
YOU WILL EXIST FOREVER.
AND WE WILL KNOW
ETERNAL LIFE TOGETHER.
- OH, MASTER.
- NOW LET US BEGIN
THE CEREMONY.
- ( ringing )
- Alastor: IF THIS INFORMATION
COMES FROM LAMIES,
THEN I BELIEVE
IT'S MOST LIKELY TRUE.
IT WOULD ALSO EXPLAIN THE
UNUSUAL NUMBER
OF TORCHES IN THE CITY.
- SHANA, LET ME BE A DECOY.
WOULDN'T THAT
DRAW OUT FRIAGNE?
WHAT'S WRONG?
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT HIM QUICKLY!
MY MOM AND FRIENDS
ARE IN DANGER!
WHY WON'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?!
WHAT IS IT?
OH, I GET IT, YOU CAN'T HELP ME
OR TALK TO ME
BECAUSE I'M NOTHING
BUT A TORCH TO YOU.
- OH, YU-CHAN.
- UH.
UH, HI, MOM.
- HELLO THERE.
SO WHO'S YOUR FRIEND.
- SHE'S, UM...
SHANA.
SHE'S ONLY A CLASSMATE.
- OH.
MAY I CALL YOU SHANA-CHAN?
WELL, YOU TWO
HAVE A GOOD TIME NOW.
- MOM, DON'T CALL HER THAT.
- WHY NOT?  WHAT'S WRONG?
OH, BY THE WAY, I'M MAKING YOUR
FAVORITE FOR SUPPER TONIGHT--
OMELET RICE--
SO DON'T BE LATE.
IT WAS VERY NICE
MEETING YOU SHANA-CHAN.
- Shana: ONLY A CLASSMATE?
I'M ONLY A FLAME HAZE,
NOTHING MORE.
IN A WAY, I'M THE SAME
AS A TORCH.
- WHY DO YOU KEEP SAYING
"ONLY"? JUST STOP IT.
- THOSE WERE HIS WORDS.
- UM, LET'S GET BACK
TO OUR CONVERSATION.
- HE'S DISGUSTING.
HE MAKES ME LOSE FOCUS
AGAIN AND AGAIN AND AGAIN.
- SHANA?
ARE YOU LISTENING?
- GET AWAY FROM ME!
- A SEAL?
SHANA?
- I WANT YOU TO STOP
CALLING ME THAT!
- WHY?
GIVE ME A REASON.
- SHUT UP!
SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
I TOLD YOU,
I'M ONLY A FLAME HAZE.
DAMN YOU.
DAMN YOU!
- AH!
- DAMN YOU!
- HUH?
- ( power surging )
- IT'S FRIAGNE.
- SHANA.  WHY?
- I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU
TO COME TO ME.
SAVES ME THE HASSLE
OF FINDING YOU.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
THE LEAST YOU COULD DO
IS SAY THANKS, LITTLE GIRL.
AH, DECIDED TO SHOW UP
WITHOUT YOUR PET MYSTES?
- WHY DON'T WE CUT
THE CHIT-CHAT?
- ( chuckles )
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
SHALL WE GET STARTED THEN?
- ( ringing )
- AAH!
- COME, LITTLE GIRL.
COME TO ME NOW.
- ( grunting )
- SHE'S FIGHTING FRIAGNE NOW.
I GUESS I'LL JUST
HAVE TO LEAVE THE REST TO HER.
I REALLY WANNA HELP HER,
BUT I CAN'T.
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
- Lamies: CAN YOU SAY
WITH COMPLETE CONFIDENCE
THAT YOU ARE
THE REAL YUJI SAKAI?
ARE YOU REALLY SATISFIED
WITH WHAT YOU ARE?
THE WAY YOU ARE NOW?
YOU APPEAR TO BE NOTHING MORE
THAN A TORCH TO ME.
- ( panting )
- ( chuckling )
DO YOU LIKE THIS TREASURE?
IT'S THE SIMPLE,
YET EFFECTIVE, BUBBLE ROOT.
HOWEVER IMPRESSIVE YOUR SWORD
MIGHT BE,
I VERY MUCH DOUBT
IT CAN BREAK THESE LINKS.
- FINE THEN.
I'LL CUT YOU INSTEAD!
- SHANA, JUMP BACK!
- ( grunting )
HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- ( grunts )
- WELL WELL,
IF I DIDN'T KNOW BETTER,
I'D THINK YOU ACTUALLY WANT ME
TO TAKE THIS TREASURE FROM YOU.
I WONDER WHAT IT IS.
- AAH!
- OH, HOW AMAZING--
A FLAME HAZE ACTUALLY
STOPPING HER SWORD IN MID-SWING.
YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO COME AFTER ME
IF YOU WANT TO GET
THIS MYSTES BACK.
I WILL PREPARE THE STAGE
FOR A FITTING FINALE.
- ( bell ringing )
- ( Friagne chuckling )
- HMM. WHEN YOU SAID
YOU HAD A PLACE IN MIND,
YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT KEISAKU'S HOUSE?
- YEAH.
IT'S A LONG STORY,
BUT THE POINT IS, HE LIVES
IN THIS HUGE HOUSE BY HIMSELF.
- WELL,
SO YOU'RE A SILVER-SPOON KID.
MUST BE NICE.
- ( chuckles )
- Marco: YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS
'CAUSE YOU AIN'T GOT A HOME!
- QUIET!
- OH!
- BUT DON'T YOU FIND IT
HARD LIVING ALONE?
I MEAN, DEALING WITH YOUR
PARENTS AND YOUR REPUTATION.
- IT'S COOL.
MY PARENTS DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
IT'S NOT AS IF MY REPUTATION
CAN GET ANY WORSE.
- I SEE.
- WHOA, AWESOME.
WHAT IS IT?
- Sato: IT'S A MAP OF MISAKI.
- I'VE COVERED THE CITY WITH AN
UNRESTRICTED METHOD NET.
WITH THIS MAP,
IF LAMIES TRIES TO GET AWAY,
I'LL SENSE HIM IMMEDIATELY.
ENOUGH TALK.
GET ME A DRINK.
- AH!
YES, MA'AM, RIGHT AWAY.
- ( distant creaking )
- ( distant explosions )
- HUH?
- THE LITTLE GIRL'S LATE,
ISN'T SHE?
I DO HOPE SHE WASN'T BLOWN APART
IN THE LAST EXPLOSION.
- SHE'LL COME.
SHANA'S A FLAME HAZE.
SHE'LL SHOW UP,
AND SHE'LL BEAT YOU!
- FOR YOUR SAKE?
- I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
- POOR FLAME HAZES,
I DO PITY THEM.
MANACLED TO THEIR MISSIONS,
FETED TO THEIR CRIMSON LORDS,
THEY WILL NEVER ESCAPE.
SUCH A POINTLESS EXISTENCE
DESERVES MY SYMPATHY.
- Shana: AW, THAT'S NICE,
BUT I DON'T REMEMBER
ASKING FOR YOUR SYMPATHY.
- SHANA, YOU'RE HERE.
- PREPARE YOURSELF.
YOUR TIME HAS COME.
- ( ringing )
- AAH!
- SHANA!
- ( ringing )
- AAH!
- Alastor: NO, DON'T! HEAD-ON
ATTACKS WON'T WORK AGAINST HIM.
- AAH!  UH.
- Yuji: THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO TO HELP HER.
- ARE YOU REALLY SATISFIED
WITH WHAT YOU ARE?
- BUT I'M--
SHANA'S FIGHTING.
I JUST FEEL SO HELPLESS.
NO, THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING I CAN DO.
SHANA, BEHIND YOU,
KICK IT!
( laughs )
- WHAT?
THIS ISN'T SOME KIND
OF GAME WE'RE PLAYING.
- Yuji: IF I CONCENTRATE,
I CAN SEE A PATTERN
TO THE BALLS OF LIGHT.
I HAVE TO TELL HER.
SHANA!  BEHIND YOU!
- SHUT UP!
- ABOVE YOU!
- SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MY BODY'S RESPONDING
AND I'M STARTING TO FEEL HOT.
- Alastor: THE INTENSITY
OF YOUR FLAME HAS INCREASED.
- Marianne: MASTER, PLEASE,
I THINK WE SHOULD STOP.
SHE'S GETTING STRONGER.
- YES, I FEEL IT TOO,
MARIANNE.
BUT WE MUST SEE THIS UNDERTAKING
THROUGH TO THE END.
WE CAN'T GIVE UP ON MY PLAN
FOR US NOW,
NOT WHEN WE'RE SO CLOSE
TO OBTAINING ETERNITY.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
THE CITY DEVOURING
WILL COMMENCE SHORTLY.
WE HAVE TO PERSEVERE
JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
- ( ringing )
( ringing continues )
- MARCOSIAS, LOOK.
- Marco: NO DOUBT ABOUT IT!
THAT BASTARD WITH THE THING
FOR DOLLS IS UP TO SOMETHING.
- IF HE KEEPS THAT UP,
I'LL NEVER FIND LAMIES,
EVEN WITH THE NET
I'VE THROWN OVER THE CITY.
- ( Marco laughing )
WANNA CRASH HIS PARTY?
- HMM.
- ( ringing )
- ( laughing )
WE'RE SO CLOSE.
JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
MY UNRESTRICTED METHOD
WILL BE COMPLETE ANY MOMENT NOW.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
- MASTER.
I PRAY FOR YOUR SAFETY,
MASTER.
PREPARE TO DIE, FLAME HAZE!
- ( screaming )
- WE'RE ALMOST THERE,
MY PRECIOUS DARLING MARIANNE.
SOON ALL OUR WISHES
WILL COME TRUE.
- ( ringing )
- THAT'S STRANGE. THOSE BIG
BALLS OF LIGHT ARE GONE,
BUT HE'S STILL RINGING
THE BELL.
AND WHY DID HE LURE SHANA
TO THIS ROOF
IF THERE'S NOTHING UP HERE?
MAYBE-- ( gasps )
MAYBE HE BROUGHT HER UP HERE
JUST TO KEEP HER DISTRACTED.
THAT MUST MEAN HE'S READY
TO START CONSUMING THE CITY.
- EVERYTHING IS IN PLACE.
THE LONG-AWAITED CITY DEVOURING
THAT WE HAVE PRAYED FOR
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
- ( ringing )
- BUT BEFORE IT STARTS,
LET'S GET RID OF HER.
WHEN A MERE TOOL FOR DESTRUCTION
DARES TO DEFY US,
THEY MUST BE PUNISHED.
- SHANA!
- STAY BACK!
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'LL USE YOUR POWER
TO OPERATE THE TRIGGER HAPPY.
- ( gasps )
AAH!
- DON'T WORRY.
I WON'T DRAIN YOU COMPLETELY.
WE DON'T WANT YOU
TO MISS THE CITY DEVOURING.
- SHANA.
- THIS SHOT WILL SIGNAL
THE BEGINNING OF
OUR ETERNITY TOGETHER, MARIANNE.
- Yuji: DON'T DO IT.
WAKE UP, SHANA.  WAKE UP.
- NOW GOOD-BYE, LITTLE GIRL.
AND FAREWELL TO THE CITY
THAT GAVE US ETERNITY.
- SHANA!
- AAH!
( panting )
IT'S NOT OVER.
THE CEREMONY FOR OUR LIFE OF
NEVER-ENDING BLISS ISN'T OVER.
IT ISN'T OVER!
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
HOW LONG WERE YOU
GONNA STRETCH THIS OUT FOR?
( blows )
- LOOK AT IT, MARIANNE.
OUR PLAN WORKED PERFECTLY.
WE'RE GOING TO BE TOGETHER NOW,
FOREVER.
AAH!
- AAH!
- AH! ( grunts )
MARIANNE,
WE'LL BE TOGETHER...
FOREVER.
- Yuji: WE WON.
- AT THE END,
IT WAS YOUR VOICE
THAT GAVE ME THE STRENGTH
I NEEDED.
- WELL, IT'S GOOD TO KNOW
I COULD BE OF SOME HELP.
MOST OF MY EXISTENCE
HAS BEEN DRAINED.
I GUESS I'M GONNA DISAPPEAR
PRETTY SOON.
I WANTED TO HELP,
EVEN THOUGH I'M ONLY A TORCH.
- DON'T SAY "ONLY."
YOU'RE YUJI SAKAI.
AND DON'T YOU FORGET IT.
- BUT I'M SORRY.
YESTERDAY YOU LOST
BECAUSE OF ME, DIDN'T YOU?
THAT'S WHY YOU TRIED
TO CUT ME.
- IT WASN'T YOU.
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
- REALLY?
I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT.
AT LEAST WHAT I DID WHILE
I WAS HERE HAD SOME MEANING.
TAKE CARE NOW, SHANA.
- ( bell tolling )
- ( gasps )
WHAT?
WHAT THE--
WHAT JUST HAPPENED TO ME?
- Alastor:
I'D SAY THAT CONFIRMS IT.
- HUH?
- THAT'S THE POWER OF THE
TREASURE INSIDE YOU,
THE MOST VALUABLE
IN ALL THE CRIMSON WORLD.
IT'S CALLED
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
AT THE FIRST STROKE
OF MIDNIGHT,
WHATEVER EXISTENCE YOU'VE LOST
DURING THE DAY FULLY RESTORED.
- SO WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- DON'T YOU GET IT YET?
IT MEANS YOU'RE STILL GONNA BE
AROUND FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- WELL,
AM I INTERRUPTING ANYTHING?
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA
MAKE ME THANK YOU, ARE YOU?
- DON'T BOTHER.
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING
TO BRING THAT STUPID FIGHT
TO AN END.
OH MY, DID I UPSET YOU?
- SOMEDAY YOU AND I ARE GONNA
SETTLE THIS, ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- HMM.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: DRIVEN BY HER HATRED
FOR ALL DENIZENS,
MARGERY DAW
RENEWS HER PURSUIT OF LAMIES.
ANOTHER CONFRONTATION
TURNS VIOLENT
WHEN SHANA GETS IN HER WAY.
NEXT EPISODE...