- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED
AND THE FLAMES
OF THE CRIMSON WORLD
SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: I GAVE THE GIRL
WHO WAS ONLY A FLAME HAZE
THE NAME SHANA.
A SMALL GESTURE,
BUT I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING
BEFORE I EVENTUALLY
DISAPPEARED FOREVER.
- Shana: HE DIDN'T EVEN ASK ME
IF I WANTED A NAME.
HE'S SO INSOLENT
FOR A TORCH.
- Alastor: A NAME.
- WHAT DO I NEED
WITH THAT KIND OF STUFF?
A NAME ISN'T GONNA HELP ME
CARRY OUT MY MISSIONS.
- Alastor:
HMM, THAT IS TRUE.
- SHA-NA.
MMM.
THAT REALLY
IS ONE STRANGE TORCH.
- UP UNTIL NOW,
EVERY TORCH EITHER
COLLAPSED IN TEARS
OR BECAME DELUSIONAL
WHILE I TRIED TO EXPLAIN
WHAT HAD HAPPENED TO THEM.
- Alastor: SOME WOULD EVEN
COMMIT SUICIDE.
- YES, BUT HE'S DIFFERENT.
BECAUSE HE'S A MYSTES?
- Alastor:
NO, A TORCH'S TEMPERAMENT
SPRINGS FROM THE ORIGINAL
PERSON'S CHARACTER.
THE FACT THAT IT'S A MYSTES
SHOULD MAKE NO REAL DIFFERENCE.
- I WONDER WHAT'S INSIDE IT.
- I DON'T KNOW YET.
BUT IT DOES NOT MATTER.
THE PROBLEM LIES
WITH THE CRIMSON DENIZENS
SEEKING TO ACQUIRE IT.
- Shana: YEAH, IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT KIND OF TORCH IT IS.
BESIDES, IT'LL BE GONE SOON.
THE RESIDUE
EVENTUALLY BURNS OUT.
IT'S GONE AND NOBODY
WILL REMEMBER ITS EXISTENCE.
THERE IS NOTHING LEFT.
- Yuji: I'M NOT GONNA FORGET.
NO MATTER WHAT.
SHE SAID SHE WAS GONNA
KEEP A CLOSE EYE ON ME.
BUT I HAVEN'T SEEN HER YET.
- GOOD MORNING.
- SAKAI.
WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY?
YOU JUST RAN OUT
OF THE GAME CENTER.
- UH, YEAH.
- YOU SAID
YOU WERE GONNA LOOK FOR HIRAI
AND THEN YOU NEVER CAME BACK.
- HUH?  WHAT?
IKE, YOU REMEMBER THAT HIRAI
WAS WITH US YESTERDAY?
- HUH?
- YOU HAVEN'T
FORGOTTEN ABOUT HER.
- WHY WOULD I FORGET HER?
SHE'S RIGHT OVER THERE.
- ( gasps )
WHAT?  BUT SHE'S...
- RELAX.
- IKE, DO ME A FAVOR.
PASS ME YOUR HOMEWORK.
- SURE.
YOU MIGHT WANNA SPLASH
SOME WATER ON YOUR FACE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I TOLD YOU,
I'M KEEPING AN EYE ON YOU.
- DID YOU HAVE TO FOLLOW ME
IN HERE?
AND YOU'RE SITTING
IN HIRAI'S DESK.
- I'M YUKARI HIRAI NOW.
- HUH?
- I DECIDED TO GO AND WORK
MYSELF INTO HER EXISTENCE.
- ( gasps )
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
- I USED SOME OF THE RESIDUE
FROM YESTERDAY.
SO RIGHT NOW,
I AM YUKARI HIRAI.
- BUT YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE--
- HIRAI, HERE'S THE NOTEBOOK
I BORROWED.
THANKS,
IT SURE CAME IN HANDY.
- THEY DON'T KNOW.
WHY NOT?
- WORKING YOURSELF
INTO SOMEONE ELSE'S EXISTENCE
HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOUR PHYSICAL APPEARANCE.
I'M REPLACING THE EXISTENCE
CALLED YUKARI HIRAI,
AND THAT'S WHAT EVERYONE SEES.
- NO WAY.
- I'M DOING THIS TO HELP ME
DEFEAT THAT DENIZEN.
YOU JUST FIND IT STRANGE
BECAUSE WE FILLED YOU IN
ON THE WHOLE PICTURE.
DON'T LET IT BOTHER YOU.
- HA.  BOTHER ME?
HIRAI JUST DISAPPEARED
YESTERDAY AND YOU'VE--
YOU'VE TAKEN OVER
LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED.
- TAKEN OVER?
LOOK, SHE WAS CONSUMED
AND DIED SOME TIME AGO.
I'M JUST MAKING USE
OF A SPACE THAT'S GOING
TO DISAPPEAR ANYWAY.
IT'S PRETTY CONVENIENT
IF YOU ASK ME.
- HA!  IT'S NOT ABOUT
WHAT'S CONVENIENT!
- ( all gasping )
- WHO IS THAT GUY?
- SAKAI?
- HOW CAN YOU BE SO
CASUAL ABOUT IT?
YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT A PERSON.
I JUST DON'T GET IT.
YOU'RE HEARTLESS!
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
CALL HER NAMES
IF YOU DON'T AGREE WITH HER.
IS THAT WHAT
HONOR STUDENTS DO?
YOU SEE, I THINK YELLING
AT A GIRL IS PRETTY OFFENSIVE.
- MM-HMM.
- MM.
- Shana: WHAT'S GOING ON?
THIS DOESN'T MAKE SENSE
TO ME.
- COME ON, WHAT ARE
YOU GUYS DOING?
GET TO YOUR SEATS.
I'M TAKING ATTENDANCE NOW.
ABE.
- HERE!
- IKE.
- HERE.
- ISHII.
- UEDA.
- HERE.
- UEHARA.
- OHBAYASHI.
- HERE.
- ( children playing )
- Yuji: IT'S NOT HER FAULT
THAT HIRAI DISAPPEARED.
AND THE ONLY REASON
SHE ASSUMED HIRAI'S IDENTITY
IS TO HELP FIGHT OUR ENEMY.
I GET THE FEELING
SHANA'S DONE THINGS
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
- ( screaming )
- IT'S LIKE SATO SAID.
IT'S JUST BECAUSE
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HER.
BUT I HAD TO SAY SOMETHING.
- ( book slams )
- MISS HIRAI!
EXPLAIN TO ME WHY YOU HAVEN'T
OPENED YOUR NOTEBOOK AND TEXT.
- ( all gasping )
- HIRAI!  ARE YOU LISTENING
TO ME, YOUNG LADY?
- Shana: HOW 'BOUT YOU LISTEN?
- ( gasping )
WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO FILL IN THE BLANK,
BUT YOU LEFT
THE WRONG PART EMPTY, SIR.
THIS ISN'T A GUESSING QUIZ.
WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO FIGURE OUT
THE MISSING WORD
- FROM THE WORDS AROUND IT.
- ( gasping )
- THE CORRECT ANSWER IS,
"THAT WHICH WE CALL A ROSE
BY ANY OTHER NAME
WOULD SMELL AS SWEET."
BUT UNLESS WE'D MEMORIZED
THE ORIGINAL TEXT WORD FOR WORD,
THERE'S NO POSSIBLE WAY
WE COULD GET THAT.
AND LOOKING
AT THE WHOLE PARAGRAPH,
IT'S FAIRLY CLEAR
YOU'VE MISSED A COUPLE OF WORDS.
- HOW-- HOW DARE YOU?
- YOU'RE JUST NOT VERY GOOD
AT EXPLAINING.
YOU TALK AND TALK
AND YOU NEVER GET TO THE POINT.
- WHAT?!
- IF YOU WANNA TEACH ME THINGS,
I SUGGEST YOU STUDY
YOUR SUBJECT PROPERLY.
- AHH!
- Student: WHO IS SHE?
- THAT'S ONE CREEPY LITTLE GIRL!
OH!
- ARE YOU SERIOUS, HIRAI?
WHAT-- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
MY CHEMICAL FORMULA
HAS A FATAL FLAW IN IT?!
AAH!  THEY DON'T PAY ME ENOUGH
FOR THIS!
I'M OUTTA HERE!
- MY EXPLANATION SOUNDS
LIKE I'M TALKING IN MY SLEEP?!
- HAVE MERCY.
( crying )
THE APOCALYPSE IS UPON US.
GOOD-BYE, CRUEL WORLD!
- Girl: HEY, WAS HIRAI
ALWAYS LIKE THAT?
- Boy: I'M NOT SURE.
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN A BIT STRANGE.
- Girl: I COULD HARDLY BREATHE.
I'M NOT EVEN THAT NERVOUS
TAKING A TEST.
- Girl #2: AND REMEMBER WHEN
SAKAI BLEW UP AT HER EARLIER?
THAT WAS WILD.
- YEAH, FOR SUCH A SWEET GUY,
HE'S GOT A REAL TEMPER.
- THAT WAS SCARY.
- SAKAI, I'VE GOT A STUDENT
COUNCIL MEETING DURING LUNCH.
- UH, THAT'S OKAY.
I'LL JUST EAT ALONE.
- I'LL SMOOTH THINGS OVER
WITH EVERYONE LATER,
BUT YOU'VE GOTTA ADMIT,
YOU WERE ACTING PRETTY WEIRD.
- YEAH, I'M SORRY.
- LATER.
- I MESSED UP.
- MM, MMM MMM.
- Alastor: IT'S BEEN
A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE SEEN YOU
IN SUCH A GOOD MOOD.
- OH, THIS MELON BREAD.
THE CRUST IS JUST RIGHT.
COMPLEMENTS THE FILLING
JUST PERFECTLY.
- MMM...
- ( sighs )
IT'S JUST LIKE
ALL THE OTHER TORCHES.
THEY GET ANGRY
OVER THE MOST TRIVIAL THINGS.
THEY ALWAYS DO. NOTHING
DIFFERENT ABOUT THIS ONE.
- HMM.
- WE'LL TAKE CARE
OF THAT CRIMSON DENIZEN,
THEN IT'S "GOOD-BYE, TORCH."
SAME AS ALWAYS.
- ( pops )
- Friagne: DO YOU REALLY
WANT TO GO, MARIANNE?
- YES.  PLEASE PERMIT ME
TO HUNT DOWN THE MYSTES FOR YOU.
I CAN'T LIVE KNOWING HOW BADLY
I FAILED YOU.
- IF THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT,
THEN REST EASY.
I'M NOT UPSET.
- BUT I HAVE TO.
MASTER, YOU ARE SO KIND.
BUT I CANNOT SIT IDLY BY.
PLEASE ACCEPT MY OFFER
TO HELP, ALONG WITH MY HEART.
- OH, MY DARLING, MARIANNE.
YOU ARE MUCH MORE
THAN I DESERVE.
I UNDERSTAND.  YOU MAY GO.
- I THANK YOU.
- BUT THERE IS THE MATTER
OF THAT FLAME HAZE
PROTECTING THE MYSTES.
TAKE THIS WITH YOU.
- RIGHT NOW I FEEL LIKE A TORCH
THAT'S ABOUT TO BURN OUT.
NOBODY WILL NOTICE
IF I JUST DISAPPEAR.
NOT ONE SINGLE PERSON
WILL REMEMBER
THAT I WAS EVER HERE.
AND THAT BOTHERS ME EVEN MORE
THAN KNOWING I'M GOING
TO VANISH FOREVER.
- Okada: PLEASE TELL ME,
WHAT ON EARTH ARE YOU TEACHING
THOSE KIDS OF YOURS,
MR. OHMINE?
THAT STUDENT, YUKARI HIRAI,
IS NOTHING BUT A TROUBLEMAKER!
- Ohmine: SO I'VE HEARD.
I DON'T SEEM TO RECALL
THAT SHE WAS ALWAYS THIS WAY.
- YOUR STUDENTS DON'T HAVE
ANY RESPECT FOR YOU.
LET'S GIVE THEM A LESSON
IN DISCIPLINE,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- RIGHT.
- Girl: SHE DIDN'T LET UP
IN THE AFTERNOON CLASSES EITHER.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HER PROBLEM IS.
- YUKARI?
SEE YA.
- HMM?
- SEE YA.
- YEAH, I HEARD YOU.
- HUH?  SORRY.
- ( sighs )
- SAKAI, I DON'T HAVE TO GO
TO PREP SCHOOL UNTIL LATER.
YOU WANNA HEAD OUT
AND GRAB A BITE?
- YOU TRYING TO CHEER ME UP?
- HUH?  NOT REALLY.
- ( voices echoing )
- THEY'RE HERE.
- HUH?
- IT'S HAPPENING
ALL OVER AGAIN.
- THEY'VE SEALED IT.
- HOLD ON.  NOT AT SCHOOL.
- THE LOCATION
IS UNIMPORTANT TO THEM.
IT'S YOU THEY'RE AFTER.
- HUH?
- I THOUGHT
YOU UNDERSTOOD THAT.
- WAIT!
EVERYONE'S STILL HERE.
- THE ENEMY SEALED THIS SPOT.
TELL IT TO THEM.
- EVERYONE'S GOING
TO BE DRAWN INTO THIS
IF I DON'T DO SOMETHING.
AND IT'LL BE MY FAULT.
EXCUSE ME.
SHANA!
- DON'T BUG ME.
- I DON'T MEAN TO DISTRACT YOU,
BUT WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN IN HERE?
- THIS ISN'T ONE OF THE MORE
IMPRESSIVE MAGIC TRICKS.
( grunting )
( screaming )
- HUH?
HA!
IKE.
IS HE ALL RIGHT?
IKE!
- ( whimpering )
- HUH, YOU'RE THE SAME RINNE
AS BEFORE.
WHAT IS YOUR MASTER'S NAME?
- YOU THINK I'D TELL YOU?
- NO, BUT I THOUGHT
I'D CHECK FIRST.
I'D SAY FROM THE WAY HE KEEPS
WASTING THE LIKES OF YOU,
HE'S PROBABLY NOT THE SMARTEST
DENIZEN IN THE CRIMSON WORLD.
- HOW DARE YOU?
- HUH?
- ( squeals )
- HELLO THERE, LITTLE ONE.
I FELT IT WAS TIME
YOU AND I MET.
- HE MUST BE ONE OF THEM.
A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
- WELL DONE.
REALLY QUITE IMPRESSIVE
THE WAY YOU REDUCED
MY "REGULAR SHARP" TREASURE
WITH NOTHING
BUT A SINGLE SWORD.
- MASTER, I'M VERY SORRY.
- NO NEED FOR APOLOGIES,
MARIANNE.
IT'S MY FAULT FOR GIVING YOU
AN UNFAMILIAR TREASURE.
- AH!
- SO YOU'RE THE MASTER.
- YES.  HUNTER FRIAGNE.
THAT IS WHAT I'M CALLED.
- HUNTER?
YOU'RE A FLAME HAZE KILLER.
- I DON'T LIKE BEING REFERRED TO
IN THAT WAY.
I SEE MYSELF AS MORE
OF A COLLECTOR OF TREASURES,
THOSE ARE WHAT I HUNT.
YOU MUST BE ALASTOR,
THE FLAME OF THE HEAVENS.
YOU'RE WELL-KNOWN
IN THE CRIMSON WORLD.
WE'VE NEVER MET, THOUGH I'D
HEARD YOU WERE ON THIS SIDE.
- Alastor: DON'T LET
HIS APPEARANCE FOOL YOU.
HE IS A POWERFUL LORD
OF THE CRIMSON WORLD.
HE COMMANDS NUMEROUS TREASURES
AND HAS OVERCOME
MANY A FLAME HAZE.
- SO THIS IS YOUR PARTNER?
THE NIETONO NO SHANA
FLAME HAZE.
SHE'S AS PRETTY AS THE RUMORS
LED ME TO BELIEVE.
ALTHOUGH I HEAR SHE HAS TROUBLE
PRODUCING HER OWN FLAMES.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- I BELIEVE YOU ARE
MERELY RELYING
ON THE POWER OF THAT
SWORD TO CALL FORTH
THE FLAMES WITHIN YOU.
AM I WRONG?
FLAME OF THE HEAVENS,
BY BINDING SOMEONE
AS WEAK AS HER TO YOU,
YOUR POWERS AS A CRIMSON LORD
ARE BEING SQUANDERED.
- YEAH?  WANNA TEST ME
AND SEE IF THAT'S THE CASE?
- I'VE SEEN THIS BEFORE.
A FLAME HAZE GETS ANGRY,
ATTACKS RECKLESSLY,
AND DIES
IN THE EXPLOSION.
I'M AFRAID I CAN'T ALLOW THAT
BECAUSE I CAN'T RISK DAMAGING
THAT VALUABLE MYSTES THERE.
- ( gasps )
- I'LL BE BACK ANOTHER TIME.
I DO WONDER
WHAT'S INSIDE IT.
WE'LL SOON SEE.
- Alastor: THIS IS A DENIZEN
WE SHOULD NOT TREAT LIGHTLY.
- I NEED TO FIX EVERYTHING
THAT'S BROKEN HERE.
MOVE OVER. I'LL USE THAT GUY.
- HMM, COME AGAIN?
- I'M GOING TO USE
THE POWER OF HIS EXISTENCE
TO FIX THE DAMAGE
TO THIS PLACE.
IKE!
YOU'RE GOING TO USE IKE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
USUALLY THERE ARE SEVERAL
TORCHES LEFT BEHIND,
BUT IN THIS CASE WE'LL HAVE
TO USE SOMEONE WHO IS DYING.
A HUMAN BEING, EVEN ONE THAT'S
DYING, IS MORE THAN ENOUGH.
WE'LL JUST REPLACE HIM
WITH A TORCH
AND THEN
THERE'LL BE NO PROBLEM.
- STOP RIGHT THERE!
YOU'RE SAYING
IKE'S GOING TO DIE LIKE ME?
- I'VE GOT NO CHOICE.
I NEED TO HAVE SOME POWER
TO FIX EVERYTHING HERE.
OKAY, WE CAN ALWAYS
USE SOMEONE ELSE.
HOW ABOUT HIM?
- STOP IT. YOU CAN'T USE
ANYONE WHO'S STILL ALIVE.
- THEN WHAT DO YOU
SUGGEST WE DO?
IF WE RELEASE THE SEAL
IN THIS STATE,
THERE'LL BE
COMPLETE CHAOS.
HE'S GOING TO DIE ANYWAY.
- BUT IT'S NOT FAIR.
I CAN'T LET THIS HAPPEN.
- WELL, DO YOU
WANNA USE YOURSELF?
THERE SHOULD BE ENOUGH FLAME
LEFT IN YOU TO FIX ALL OF THIS.
BUT THAT MEANS YOU'RE ONLY GONNA
BURN OUT THAT MUCH QUICKER.
THERE'S NO WAY
HE'S GONNA DO IT.
HE'S JUST LIKE
ANY OTHER TORCH.
THEY'RE DESPERATE TO HANG ON
TO WHAT LITTLE EXISTENCE
THEY HAVE LEFT.
- Yuji: YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT IS AN OPTION.
MY EXISTENCE WILL BE USED
TO HELP IKE AND THE OTHERS.
THAT'LL BE PROOF
THAT I WAS HERE.
- HMM.
- SO STRANGE.
NO, PECULIAR.
NO, SICKENING.
YES.
HE'S SICKENING.
- Alastor:
BUT THAT DIDN'T STOP YOU
FROM USING YOUR POWERS.
- WHAT ELSE COULD I DO?
HE ACTUALLY OFFERED
TO LET ME USE HIS EXISTENCE.
HE'S LUCKY I DIDN'T USE UP
ALL OF HIS FLAME.
HUH?
- HEY THERE.
I KNEW YOU'D BE UP HERE.
- AREN'T YOU SMART?
- Alastor: HOW DID YOU
KNOW WE WERE HERE?
- I FELT SOMETHING,
KINDA LIKE THAT SEALED ZONE
TODAY, BUT A LOT SMALLER.
- REALLY? I SUPPOSE YOU'RE
BEGINNING TO DEVELOP A FEELING
FOR THE POWER
AFTER REPEATED EXPOSURE TO IT.
- SAY, I'VE BEEN WONDERING,
IS THAT THING
LIKE A TRANSMITTER?
- HMM.
- SIMILAR, BUT DIFFERENT.
THIS IS CALLED THE COCYTUS.
IT ACTS AS A MIRROR
FOR MY CONSCIOUSNESS,
WHICH IS PRESENTLY RESIDING
WITHIN THIS GIRL.
- OKAY.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND.
- GREAT.  HAPPY NOW?
- UH, NO.  I JUST WANTED
TO SAY THANKS AND APOLOGIZE.
- THANKS AND APOLOGIZE?
WHAT DID I DO TO DESERVE THAT?
- I'M REALLY SORRY
FOR YELLING AT YOU ABOUT HIRAI.
AND THANK YOU
FOR NOT USING IKE.
- HUH? I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE BIG DEAL IS
BECAUSE I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER
YOU YELLING AT ME.
AND ALL I DID
WAS USE YOUR EXISTENCE
INSTEAD OF
YOUR FRIEND'S EXISTENCE.
SO YOUR FLAME
IS MUCH SMALLER NOW.
IT COULD GO OUT AT ANY TIME.
- YES, BUT IT'S STILL BETTER
THAN WAITING
FOR THE END TO COME
AND THEN BEING FORGOTTEN.
I THINK MY EXISTENCE,
MY MEMORY,
IS A PART
OF IKE AND THE OTHERS NOW.
- BUT IT'S NO DIFFERENT
FROM ANY OTHER MEMORY.
IT'LL JUST GET BURIED UNDER
ALL THE EVENTS THAT ARE TO COME.
- BUT IT'LL BE THERE.
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME.
HERE, THIS IS FOR YOU.
- IT'S BITTER!
- OH, BUT I ADDED SUGAR.
- SPOON!
- OH, I FORGOT.
I'LL GO GET ONE.
- DAMN IT.
WHY DOES HE BUG ME SO MUCH?
HMM?
DID YOU SEE THAT?
- HMM. I THINK I KNOW
WHAT THE TREASURE
INSIDE THIS MYSTES
MIGHT BE.
- Yuji: I KNEW NOTHING
AT THE TIME.
I HAD NO IDEA
WHAT WAS INSIDE ME.
AND I CERTAINLY DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT THE PEOPLE
WHO HAD JUST ARRIVED
IN MISAKI.
- Margery: HA!  DULLSVILLE.
- ( Marco laughing )
YOU SAID THE SAME THING
ABOUT ALL THOSE
EUROPEAN TOWNS TOO.
MAYBE DULL IS ONLY IN THE EYE
OF THE BEHOLDER,
MY DEARLY BELOVED GOBLET,
MARGERY DAW!
( laughing, grunting )
- STAY FOCUSED.
WE KNOW FOR A FACT
THIS IS WHERE HE RAN TO.
AND I'M PICKING UP
OTHER SCENTS AS WELL.
- YES, SOMETHING DOES SMELL.
AND IT'S YOUR BREATH,
YOU BOOZEHOUND! ( laughing )
- OW!
- QUIET, STUPID MARCO.
I THINK THIS COULD BECOME
VERY INTERESTING INDEED.
- HA.  WE HAVE PESTS.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: IMPATIENT, HESITANT,
SHANA BEGINS
TO QUESTION HER FEELINGS.
BEFORE A RESOLUTION
CAN BE REACHED,
A BATTLE
BETWEEN FLAME HAZES BREAKS OUT.
NEXT EPISODE...