- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
( screams in pain )
- ( screaming )
- HUH?
- WHAT? WHAT IS THAT?
I, I FOUND IT.
THE PALACE OF HEAVEN'S ROAD.
- WE HAVE A REAL
EMERGENCY INDEED.
- MIGHTY WARRIOR,
I AM HERE TO FIGHT YOU.
- FROZEN WITH FEAR I SEE.
- INDEED, WE MUST RETURN
AT ONCE.
- Tiamat: Agreed.
- YOU DON'T ACTUALLY THINK
YOU'LL ESCAPE, DO YOU?
- ( footsteps approaching )
- Hmm?
- WHAT?
- THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING...
- ( groans )
- SHIRO.
IS THIS MY FAULT?
THIS HAPPENED...
BECAUSE I TRICKED HIM?
- ( sobs ) I'M SORRY.
I JUST WANTED TO SHOW YOU.
I WANTED TO SHOW YOU
THAT I COULD DO IT.
THAT I COULD BEAT YOU
IF I PUT MY MIND TO IT.
- ( crying ) SHIRO,
I AM SO SORRY. SHIRO.
- WELL LOOK HERE. I THINK
I'VE FOUND THE CULPRIT.
- ( laughing )
I DON'T KNOW ALL THE DETAILS,
BUT WHATEVER YOU DID, THANKS.
- HUMAN? NO, HE'S...
A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
- YEAH, SO?
WHAT'S WITH THE SOUR FACE?
HEY, NOW I'VE GOT
A LITTLE QUESTION.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- WHAT ARE YOU?
- I AM...
- YEAH, I AM. WHAT?
- I'M TRAINING... TO BECOME
A FLAME, FLAME HAZE.
- ( laughs )
- SO, YOU WANT TO
BE A FLAME HAZE.
PERFECT, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I WANTED TO HEAR.
I'M ALWAYS ON THE LOOKOUT
FOR PEOPLE LIKE YOU.
PREVENTING THE REINSTATEMENT
OF A CONTRACT
IS A GREAT
ACCOMPLISHMENT,
ESPECIALLY IF IT'S THE
FLAMING-HAIRED BLAZING-EYED ONE.
- IT'S JUST LIKE ALASTOR SAID,
HE'S MANIPULATING THE
POWER OF EXISTENCE.
HE HAS THE ABILITY TO DRAW IT
FROM HUMAN BEINGS.
SO IS THAT HOW YOU EAT PEOPLE?
- YEAH, THIS IS
HOW I ALWAYS DO IT.
- HE ALWAYS DOES IT.
HE'S THE ENEMY.
- HMM, WHAT'S THIS?
YOU'RE TREMBLING.
- ( groans )
- GOODBYE. I HOPE YOU HAVE
BETTER LUCK IN YOUR NEXT LIFE.
- ( laughs )
- NOW I SEE. IT'S CLEAR.
THIS IS RIGHT. I'VE MADE
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
I'VE DECIDED TO BECOME
A FLAME HAZE. GOT THAT?
I WILL BE A FLAME HAZE. I WILL.
- NOT IN THIS
LIFETIME YOU WON'T.
- ( screams )
- INDEED, I SEE I
AM NOT TOO LATE.
- WIRHELMINA.
- YOU CAN TELL ME
ALL ABOUT IT LATER.
INDEED IT'S TIME FOR CHANGES...
FOR EVERYONE.
- PLEASE DON'T BLAME
SHIRO FOR THIS.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT. I DID IT.
- INDEED I'VE NO INTENTION
OF BLAMING HIM
FOR WHAT HAS TRANSPIRED.
NOW THAT A DENIZEN HAS FOUND IT,
WE CAN NO LONGER LIVE
IN THIS PLACE.
TO STAY AND TO TRY
AND CONTINUE OUR LIVES
AS WE KNEW IT,
WOULD BE POINTLESS.
- DON'T SAY THAT.
I DON'T WANNA HEAR THAT.
I WANNA BE A FLAME HAZE.
I DO, I DO.
IT'S ALL I WANT.
MY TRAINING CAN'T BE OVER,
PLEASE WIRHELMINA,
SAY IT ISN'T SO.
- YOU MISUNDERSTAND.
IT SEEMS YOU HAVE INDEED
MISSED THE POINT HERE.
- I HAVE?
- YOUR TRAINING'S OVER BECAUSE
YOU'RE GOING TO BE JUST FINE.
- HUH?
- YOU NO LONGER NEED TO TRAIN,
NOR TO LIVE WITHIN THE WALLS
OF THIS PALACE BECAUSE INDEED
YOUR LIFE AS A FLAME HAZE
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
- REALLY?
- ( coughing )
- ( Screams )
- SHIRO.
- INDEED, OTHER ENEMIES FOLLOW.
YOU ARE TO STAY HERE,
AND DO THE BEST YOU
CAN TO HOLD THEM BACK.
YOU NEED TO BUY US SOME TIME.
- WIRHELMINA.
- WE HAVE TO BE GOING.
- NOT SO FAST.
BASTARD.
- AREN'T YOU WORRIED
ABOUT SHIRO?
- NO.
- Shana: UM, WIRHELMINA,
ARE YOU, YOU KNOW...
ARE YOU A FLAME HAZE?
- THAT IS, INDEED, WHAT I AM.
I AM THE FLAME HAZE OF TIAMAT,
THE TIARA OF DREAMS
AND ILLUSIONS.
MY NAME IS WIRHELMINA CARMEL,
THE SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING.
- Tiamat: GREETINGS.
- HUH?
- THAT'S HER. THAT WAS
THE VOICE OF A DENIZEN OF
THE CRIMSON REALM, TIAMAT.
INDEED, SHE IS NOT WHAT YOU
WOULD CALL THE SOCIABLE TYPE.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME ABOUT THIS?
- I DID THIS TO MAKE
SURE THAT YOU WOULD
HAVE NO PRECONCEPTIONS.
- I WANTED YOU TO ENVISION
WHAT YOU WANTED TO BE.
AND THEN, INDEED, DEVELOP
THAT VISION IN YOUR OWN HEART.
THOUGH IT SEEMS I DIDN'T
HAVE ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
- WELL, I GUESS IT WORKED THEN,
BECAUSE I REALLY WANNA
BE A FLAME HAZE.
AREN'T YOU AT LEAST
A LITTLE PROUD OF ME?
- INDEED I CAN'T
THINK OF A MOMENT
WHEN I WASN'T PROUD OF YOU.
- ( sobs ) I CAN FEEL IT. YOU
ARE PROUD OF ME,
AREN'T YOU, WIRHELMINA?
AND IT'S ALL THANKS TO YOU.
- THAT IS CORRECT INDEED.
- HUH?
- ( screams )
- OH NO, THIS CAN'T BE
HAPPENING. WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
JUST MY LUCK TO HAVE THE
NEMESIS
OF THE ENTIRE CRIMSON
WORLD SHOW UP.
IT'S TENMOKUIKKO.
- Wirhelmina: INDEED, OUR
LATEST GUEST IS TENMOKUIKKO.
- Shana: WHO'S HE?
- THE MOST FEARED MYSTES EVER.
INDEED, THOSE WHO SURVIVE
THE ENCOUNTER CALL HIM
THE MONSTER OF ALL TORCHES.
HE'S NIGH INVINCIBLE,
AND INDEED OVER THE YEARS
HE HAS MADE HIS REPUTATION
SLAUGHTERING
COUNTLESS POWERFUL DENIZENS.
IT WOULD BE DANGEROUS
TO APPROACH HIM RECKLESSLY.
- Tiamat: DELAYED DEFENSE.
- ROGER THAT.
- Vine: DON'T COME
NEAR ME. DON'T.
DON'T COME ANY CLOSER.
STAY BACK!
- ( yells ) STAY BACK.
- EVERYTHING WAS GOING
SO WELL FOR ME.
BUT THEN THIS, WHY?
I DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HIM.
WAIT. WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ORGON?
THIS MONSTER MUST HAVE
DEFEATED HIM. NOW I SEE.
HE'S THE ONE WHO'S BEEN KILLING
THE MEMBERS OF THE BALL MASQUE.
LADY BEL PEOL,
PLEASE PROTECT ME.
- Shana: HOW DID HE GET HERE?
- Wirhelmina: I THINK
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
HE WAS ABLE TO FIND US.
INDEED THE PALACE MUST
HAVE BEEN REVEALED
WHEN THE RAINBOW SKY SWORD
DESTROYED THE OUTER SHELL.
- WAS THE RAINBOW SKY SWORD,
THE RAINBOW SHIRO PULLED OUT?
- WAIT, WHERE'S SHIRO?
- HE'S DOING JUST FINE.
HE DID EVERYTHING HE COULD
UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
- BUT THINGS HAVE CHANGES,
SO HE'S KEEPING STILL.
- HE'S NOT DEAD?
- HIS LIFE IS BOUND BY
A SOLEMN OATH.
THEREFORE IT IS INDEED
IMPOSSIBLE FOR HIM
TO DIE BEFORE THE
VOW IS FULFILLED.
- WHY IS TENMOKUIKKO TAKING SO
LONG TO FINISH OFF THAT DENIZEN?
- I BELIEVE IT IS BECAUSE
HE HAS SENSED
THE PRESENCE OF A MUCH
GREATER TARGET.
- THE FLAME OF HEAVEN.
- Tiamat: AGREED.
- HE WANTS TO FIGHT ALASTOR,
BECAUSE HE'S THE
STRONGEST DENIZEN HERE.
- Wirhelmina: I WILL KEEP
THAT OTHER DENIZEN AT BAY,
AS WELL AS ANYONE ELSE WHO MIGHT
FOLLOW, FOR AS LONG AS I CAN.
- SO I CAN MAKE A CONTRACT
WITH, WITH ALASTOR.
- IF BOTH OF YOU ARE
IN AGREEMENT,
THE CONTRACT WILL BE ENACTED
INSTANTANEOUSLY.
AFTER THAT, ALL YOU
HAVE TO DO IS FOLLOW
THE FLAME OF HEAVEN'S
INSTRUCTIONS.
THEN YOU WILL EMBARK ON
YOUR MISSION AS A FLAME HAZE.
RIGHT NOW THE MAIN PROBLEM
ISN'T YOUR DETERMINATION,
BUT IT'S WHETHER OR NOT I CAN
HOLD THEM BACK LONG ENOUGH
FOR YOU TO ACTUALLY
REACH THAT STAGE.
- CAN YOU DEAL WITH
THAT DENIZEN ALONE?
- I SURMISE FROM THE AMOUNT
OF ENERGY HE EMITS THAT
THE ODDS OF VICTORY
ARE INDEED IN MY FAVOR.
- AGREED.
- TELL ME ABOUT TENMOKUIKKO.
TELL ME EVERYTHING YOU KNOW.
- WHAT SHOULD I DO?
IF I MAKE A WRONG MOVE,
HE'LL SPLIT ME IN TWO.
- Wirhelmina: TENMOKUIKKO.
- THE FOOL. THAT'S SUICIDE.
WHAT THE...
SOMEHOW THAT LITTLE GIRL
KNOWS HE NEVER ATTACKS HUMANS.
- Shana: TENMOKUIKKO,
WHAT IS IT YOU WANT?
IF YOU WANT TO HAVE A DUEL WITH
A REAL FLAME HAZE,
THEN YOU MUST ACT AS MY ESCORT.
IF YOU AGREE, THEN I SWEAR
I WILL ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE
AND FIGHT YOU AS THE FLAME-
HAIRED BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
- FLAMING-HAIR BLAZING-EYES.
- YES.
- YOU HAVE THE POTENTIAL
TO BECOME A MIGHTY WARRIOR.
I WILL FIGHT YOU.
- I WON'T LET YOU.
- INDEED, I AM TO
BE YOUR OPPONENT.
- ( groans )
- SO BE IT.
NEXT TIME I SEE YOU...
- I'LL KILL YOU. I SHALL SLAY
EVERYONE WHO DARE TO INSULT ME.
EVERYONE SHALL DIE.
- Alastor: IT IS HERE.
THE TIME HAS COME.
- WHEN YOU ENTER INTO
THE CONTRACT,
I WANT YOU TO SHOW THE
FLAME OF HEAVEN
THE FEELINGS YOU HAVE
HIDDEN AWAY IN YOUR HEART.
- I UNDERSTAND.
I HAVE DECIDED THAT TODAY
I WILL ACCEPT EVERYTHING
AND ANYTHING THAT I SEE.
I WILL REVEAL MY HIDDEN
FEELINGS AND HOLD NOTHING BACK,
BECAUSE IF I HAVE TO SHOW THEM
TO ANYONE, IT SHOULD BE ALASTOR.
- Wirhelmina: YES.
- LET'S GO.
- WHEN YOU'RE THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER,
THE GLITTERING FLAMES
WILL LOOK GOOD ON YOU INDEED.
- HURRY UP.
THE FASTER YOU MOVE, THE SOONER
YOU'LL HAVE YOUR DUEL.
- FLAME HAZES ARE INDEED
BY NATURE A RATHER SINFUL LOT.
HESITATION AND MERCY
ARE UNNECESSARY.
- PERSONA GOD VESSEL.
- Tiamat: UNDERSTOOD.
- NO DEFECTS.
- Tiamat: CHECKED.
- YOU ARE THE
SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING.
- INDEED, I HAVE ALWAYS WANTED
TO FACE YOU IN BATTLE.
- Tiamat: COMMENCE.
- Alastor: LET US BEGIN.
- Shana: THIS WILL
ONLY TAKE A MOMENT.
- ( screams )
- Alastor: HURRY
WITH THE CONTRACT.
- WIRHELMINA TOLD ME TO TELL YOU
WHAT I'VE BEEN HIDING FROM YOU.
- HMM?
- YOU'RE KEEPING SECRETS
FROM ME, TOO.
- MY HUNTER IS DESTINED
TO CARRY A HIDDEN TREASURE,
THE TENPAJYOSAI.
- AND THE FLAME HAZE THAT
USES IT, IS DESTROYED BY IT.
- GOODBYE.
MAY YOUR FLAMES LAST
FOR ETERNITY AND NEVER DIM.
I LOVE YOU ALASTOR,
FLAME OF HEAVEN.
- Alastor: IF NECESSARY,
MY CONTRACTOR IS TO USE
THE SECRET METHOD
TO ACCOMPLISH THEIR MISSION.
YOU WOULD HAVE WALKED
ANOTHER PATH IN LIFE,
YET WE HAVE BOUND
YOU TO THIS DESTINY,
WITH NOTHING BUT OUR LOVE.
- I KNOW. I LOVE YOU TOO.
I LOVE ALL OF YOU.
YOU NEVER WANTED
TO USE IT, DID YOU?
THAT METHOD WAS A LAST RESORT.
WHEN YOU TALK OF THE
PREVIOUS FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER,
YOU SOUND SO HAPPY...
AND SAD AT THE SAME TIME.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR TELLING ME ABOUT IT,
BUT IT'S FINE. I'VE DECIDED
THAT THIS IS RIGHT FOR ME.
THIS IS MY PATH. I WILL
CARRY OUT MY MISSION,
EVEN AT THE COST OF MY LIFE.
THAT IS WHAT FLAME HAZES DO.
THE FEELINGS I HAVE BEEN HIDING
ARE FROM BEFORE.
I HAVE ALWAYS HAD THESE
DOUBTS ABOUT THIS
GREAT CAUSE IN WHICH FLAME HAZES
DO BATTLE WITH CRIMSON
DENIZENS TO MAINTAIN
THE BALANCE OF THE WORLD.
- Alastor: I SEE.
- Shana: IT MAY BE OR
MAY NOT BE TRUE
BUT THE ONLY WAY I'LL
KNOW FOR SURE IS IF
I FIND OUT ON MY OWN.
I'M SORRY ALASTOR.
I KNOW I'M BEING DIFFICULT.
I KNOW YOU CARE BUT NO MATTER
HOW MUCH YOU LOVE ME
AND NO MATTER HOW MUCH
I LOVE EVERYONE ELSE IN RETURN,
IF YOU'RE UNCOMFORTABLE WITH
THIS, THEN I JUST CAN'T DO IT.
HE'S GETTING IN THE WAY.
KILL HIM.
- ( screams )
- OH MAGNIFICENT CRIMSON LORD,
FLAME OF HEAVEN, ALASTOR,
I RESPECT YOUR WILL.
BE INCARNATED USING MY
BODY AS YOUR VESSEL.
TOGETHER WE SHALL CARRY OUT
THE MISSION OF THE FLAME HAZES
UNTIL THE DAY WE FALL.
ALASTOR, THIS IS YOU.
YOUR FLAMES ARE SO HOT.
YOU, YOU ARE THE
FLAME OF HEAVEN.
- Alastor: CHOOSE
YOUR GOD VESSEL.
- A PENDANT,
SO THAT YOU WILL BE LIKE A
CLEAR AND UNCLOUDED EYE
WATCHING OVER US.
- Alastor: HMM.
I WELCOME YOUR ARRIVAL TO
THE SCENE OF CARNAGE,
TO THE GARDENS OF BATTLE,
MY FLAME HAZE.
- YOU ARE WELCOME IN ME,
ALASTOR, THE FLAME OF HEAVEN,
FOR I AM NOW A FLAME HAZE.
FLAMING HAIR AND BLAZING EYES.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: IT WAS A PROMISE
FROM A DAY LONG, LONG AGO
BETWEEN THOSE HOLDING THE FLAME
AND THE GIRL WHO WAS
ABOUT TO RECEIVE IT.
THEN, THE END OF
THE BEGINNING ARRIVES.
NEXT EPISODE,
"THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER."