- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: DURING AN INTENSE BATTLE
WITH A FLAME HAZE
KNOWN AS THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES,
SHANA RISES TO THE OCCASION
AND DISCOVERS NEW POWERS
WITHIN HER.
SHE EMERGES VICTORIOUS
AND BOTH FRIEND AND FOE
BID EACH OTHER FAREWELL.
AFTER A STRUGGLE LIKE THAT,
IT'S ONLY NATURAL
TO TAKE A BREAK.
BUT AT THE TIME,
I HAD NO WAY OF KNOWING
THAT SHANA'S NEXT BATTLE
WAS JUST AROUND THE CORNER.
- Lamies: DON'T GO AFTER SILVER.
- ( gasps )
- YOU'D BE WASTING YOUR TIME.
- GO EASIER.
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
ASKED FOR LESSONS.
- YEAH, I KNOW, BUT STILL.
- NO, IT'S JUST A COINCIDENCE.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE I'M WRONG.
- MAN, IT'S REALLY SCORCHING.
HOW CAN IT BE THIS HOT
SO EARLY IN THE MORNING?
- WELL, IT'S SUMMERTIME, YUJI.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE HOT.
- YEAH, I KNOW, BUT--
- I THINK YOU SHOULD PUT MORE OF
YOUR HEART INTO YOUR TRAINING.
WE'VE BEEN TRAINING
EVERY MORNING,
BUT YOU HAVEN'T IMPROVED
ONE BIT.
- ( clanging )
- HEY, GIVE ME A BREAK.
SOME PEOPLE ARE NATURALLY
GIFTED, BUT I'M NOT.
- Alastor: HMM, ALREADY LOOKING
FOR AN EXCUSE.
- HE'S SAYING WE JUST STARTED,
SO DON'T TRY TALKING
YOUR WAY OUT OF THE LESSONS.
WE'LL HAVE A BETTER IDEA
OF WHETHER YOU'RE GIFTED OR NOT
ONCE YOU'VE LEARNED TO MOVE
ABOUT A LITTLE MORE NATURALLY.
YOU NEED TO FOCUS MORE.
- HEY, WAIT UP!
SHANA!
- YO, THANKS, DUDE!
- THANKS A LOT, IKE!
- HEY, MAN,
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
- HI. CHECK IT, I SCORED A
BUNCH OF THESE FREE PASSES.
MY DAD'S CONNECTIONS AT WORK
GOT HIM ALL THESE TICKETS
TO MISAKI WATERLAND.
I THOUGHT I'D HAD 'EM OUT
TO THE CLASS.
- ALL RIGHT!
MISAKI WATERLAND!
THAT'S THE PLACE WITH THOSE
COMMERCIALS-- "GET WET!" RIGHT?
- Female Announcer: GET YOUR
BIKINIS ON! MISAKI WATERLAND!
- All: GET WET!
- AW, YEAH!
I FIGURED THESE WOULD
GO OVER PRETTY WELL.
- THEY'RE GONNA LOVE IT.
WAY TO GO, IKE!
- HERE'S YOURS, HIRAI.
- ( bell tolling )
- WE SHOULD GET
NEW BATHING SUITS.
- YEAH, LET'S GO SHOPPING.
- MMM.
THERE'S HIS STUNNED LOOK
AGAIN.
- HEY, SHANA,
WE'VE BOTH GOT FREE TICKETS.
YOU WANNA GO CHECK THIS PLACE
OUT TOMORROW OR WHAT?
HUH? SHANA?
- HMM?
WHAT?  WHAT IS IT?
YOU CAN'T HAVE A COMPLAINT.
WE HAVEN'T
EVEN STARTED CLASS YET.  DOH!
- YOUR NECKTIE SUCKS.
- WHAT?
HMM?
IT'S IN STYLE!
- ( sighs )
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YUJI?
HIS FACE GETS ALL SLACK OVER A
STUPID PICTURE LIKE THIS.
- Alastor: A TICKET
TO A PLACE OF SWIMMING?
- I GUESS SO.
- FOR SOME REASON, HUMAN BEINGS
LIKE TO PLAY AROUND IN WATER.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL THEY WOULD
SEE IT AS A LEISURE ACTIVITY.
- THAT'S NO EXCUSE FOR LETTING
HIS FACE GET ALL LOOSE.
NO WONDER HE CAN'T FOCUS
ON HIS TRAINING.
- Alastor: HMM.
- I WAS WONDERING, ALASTOR.
- Alastor: WHAT IS IT?
- DO YOU THINK
THIS WATERLAND PLACE
FEELS AS GOOD AS A BATH DOES?
- Alastor: I HAVE NO IDEA.
- YEAH, I GUESS NOT.
HMM.
- ( bell tolling )
- Boy:
HEY, LET'S EAT ON THE ROOF.
- SHANA'S BEEN GONE
FOR THE WHOLE MORNING.
- Girl:
HI, WHERE'D YOU GO, HIRAI?
- Shana:
I WENT OUT.
- WHERE WERE YOU THIS MORNING?
- I WENT TO A BAKERY.
- UH, A BAKERY?
- MMM.
MMM!
AH, THE BEST YET!
YOU HAVE TO GET
JUST THE RIGHT COMBINATION
OF CRISP AND SPONGY
FOR THE PERFECT MELON BREAD.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- WELL, SURE, IF YOU SAY SO.
- UH, IT'S JUST--
I WAS--
- HMM?
- IT'S JUST-- I-- I WAS THINKING
WE COULD ALL SIT TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW,
AND EAT OUR LUNCHES.
- MMM.
- THIS IS NICE FOR A CHANGE,
ISN'T IT?
DON'T YOU FIND FRIENDS
AND GOOD CONVERSATION
MAKE FOOD TASTE BETTER?
BETTER THAN EATING ALONE.
- MM-HMM.
FOR SURE.
- I--
AAH!
- HMM?
- I-- I MEAN--
THAT IS--
YA SEE, WELL--
I-- IT'S JUST--
SAKAI!
- UH, WHAT IS IT?
- WELL, I WAS WONDERING, YOU--
YOU ALWAYS BRING RICE BALLS
FROM THE CONVENIENCE STORE
FOR YOUR LUNCH.
- YEAH, IT'S MY MOM.
SHE SAYS A MAN WHO COUNTS ON HIS
MOTHER FOR THREE MEALS A DAY
ISN'T GONNA GO VERY FAR IN LIFE,
OR SOMETHING ALONG THOSE LINES.
- SHE SAYS THAT?
- YEAH.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST SAY IT?
YOU WERE GONNA INVITE HIM TO
MISAKI WATERLAND, WEREN'T YOU?
- BUT-- BUT IT'S HARD.
- GUYS! I JUST HAD A GREAT IDEA!
SINCE IKE WAS NICE ENOUGH
TO GIVE US THESE TICKETS,
WHY DON'T WE ALL GO TO WATERLAND
THIS SUNDAY AS A GROUP?
- OGATA, "ALL OF US" MEANS...
EVERYONE?
- YEAH!  WELL, OF COURSE
I DON'T MEAN THE WHOLE CLASS!
BUT EVERYONE HERE FOR SURE.
AND...
MMM, WHAT ABOUT THOSE TWO
OVER THERE?
- All: HUH?  MMM.
- I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, SAKAI?
- UH, SURE,
SOUNDS GREAT.
- HOW 'BOUT YOU, HIRAI?
- MMM?
- IT WOULDN'T BE THE SAME IF OUR
CLASS HEROINE DIDN'T COME ALONG.
- HMM?  YOU WANT ME?
- YEAH, WHY NOT?
LET'S GO.
- SURE, I GUESS.
- THEN IT'S SETTLED!
- HUH?
- WE'LL MEET THERE
10:00 SUNDAY!
AND YOU TWO GUYS
BETTER NOT BE LATE.
YOU'VE GOT A REAL REPUTATION
FOR NEVER BEING ON TIME.
- WE'RE NOT GOIN'.
SORRY.
WE DECIDE WHERE WE GO.
- OGA-CHAN, SORRY,
WE'VE GOT PLANS.
MAYBE NEXT TIME.
- SHOOT.
- YOU KNOW, I KINDA FEEL BAD
FOR OGA-CHAN.
- IT COULDN'T BE HELPED.
DON'T FORGET, WE'RE BUSY
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO INSISTED WE TAKE MARGERY
SOMEWHERE HEALTHY THIS WEEKEND.
- I KNOW.
I DON'T REALLY UNDERSTAND IT.
BUT EVER SINCE SHE CAME BACK,
SHE'S DONE NOTHING
BUT STAY INSIDE AND DRINK.
WE NEED TO HELP HER.
SHE'S GONNA MAKE HERSELF SICK
IF SHE DOESN'T GET OUT
AND HAVE SOME FUN.
HUH?
- Marco:
WELCOME HOME, YOU TWO.
SHE'S BEEN AN IDIOT
AGAIN TODAY,
MY SLEEPING PRINCESS
OF OVERINDULGENCE, MARGERY DAW.
- HELLO.
YOU BOYS ARE HOME EARLY.
THAT'S A FACT.
( laughs, snores )
- UGH.
- HOW DOES THAT ONE LOOK?
- Yoshida: GOOD, IT'S
NOT TOO SHOWY.
I COULD WEAR THIS.
- ( laughs )
- HUH?
OGATA?
- ( laughs )
- OGATA?
( gasps )
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- LOOK, YOU'RE GOING
TO THE POOL WITH BOYS.
DON'T WEAR SOMETHING BORING.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING YOUR CLOTHES
BACK UNTIL YOU TRY IT ON.
- I CAN'T!
- I'M DOING THIS AS A FRIEND!
COME ON,
HURRY UP AND PUT IT ON.
- OKAY.
- WELL, ARE YOU READY?
- ALMOST.
- ARE YOU READY NOW?
- YEAH, I GUESS.
BUT--
- THEN HURRY UP AND SHOW ME!
- AAH!
- WOW!
- OGATA!
HAVE MERCY!
- THIS ONE NEXT!
OR WOULD YOU RATHER
TRY THIS ONE ON?
- I'D RATHER GO
IN A REGULAR ONE-PIECE, THANKS.
- Chigusa: HERE YOU ARE, SHANA-
CHAN. I GOT YOU A SWIMSUIT.
I KNOW
YOU HAVE A SUIT FOR P.E.,
BUT I THOUGHT YOU'D WANNA WEAR
SOMETHING A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
- OH, WHY'S THAT?
- BECAUSE THEN YOU CAN WEAR
SOMETHING CUTE,
NOT LIKE THE STANDARD ONES
AT SCHOOL.
- MMM.
- WHY DON'T YOU TRY IT ON?
- SURE.
- HMM?  UH...
- HMM?
( grunting )
- IT'S BEST
IF YOU WAIT OUT HERE.
- Alastor: DIDN'T YOU LEARN
ANYTHING FROM THE LAST TIME?
- IT WAS A MISUNDERSTANDING.
- MAN, IT'S GIGANTIC!
- HAVING ONE OF THESE CLOSE BY
MAKES THE SUMMERS BEARABLE.
- IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
TANAKA AND SATO ARE COMING.
THEY'RE NOT EVEN ANSWERING
THE PHONE.
- HMM.
- WELL, WHO CARES
IF THEY DECIDED
THEY HAD SOMETHING BETTER
TO DO?
THE FIVE OF US
WILL HAVE A BLAST!
- IT'LL BE GREAT!
- HMM.
- WHAT IS IT?
- LOOK AT THIS POSTER.
- "COUPLE'S WATER COMPETITION."
- LET'S SEE HERE--
"MIXED COUPLE TEAMS
WILL COMPETE AGAINST EACH OTHER
IN THE POOL.
THE WINNING TEAM WILL RECEIVE
AN ALL-EXPENSES PAID DINNER,
WITH ALL THE FRESH BREAD
YOU CAN EAT,
AT AN EXCLUSIVE RESTAURANT
WITH A NIGHT VIEW."
- ALL THE FRESH BREAD
YOU CAN EAT?
- DINNER FOR TWO
AT A FANCY RESTAURANT?
- HERE'S TO YOUR BEAUTIFUL EYES.
- OH, THANK YOU.
( sighs )
- LOOKS LIKE FUN!
IT DOESN'T START TILL THIS
AFTERNOON. WHO'S UP FOR IT.
- I'LL DO IT.
- I WANNA GIVE IT A TRY TOO.
- HUH?
- THEN IT'S SETTLED.
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH BOYS,
BUT WE'LL DEAL
WITH THAT PROBLEM LATER.
- HMM.
OH, THAT'S HER!
- ( giggling )
SORRY FOR THE WAIT!
- WHERE ARE YOSHIDA AND HIRAI?
- RELAX, THEY'RE COMING.
LET ME PRESENT,
WITHOUT FURTHER ADO,
THE YUKARI AND KAZUMI
SWIMSUIT FASHION SHOW.
FIRST, MISS HIRAI!
COME ON OUT!
- ( both sigh )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- Both: NOTHING'S WRONG.
- AND MISS YOSHIDA.
COME ON OUT!
- All: HMM?
- KAZUMI?
- MMM.
HEY, OGATA, I REALLY
DON'T THINK I CAN DO THIS.
- ( grunting )
GO!  GET OUT THERE!
- OH OH!
- Both: AH!
- HMM.
- IT IS SO HOT!
I'M DYING.
- BIG SISTER,
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
YOU'RE GONNA GET SICK IF YOU
STAY INDOORS ALL THE TIME.
- I'LL BE DEAD
IF I STAY OUT HERE MUCH LONGER.
- YOU MAY BE RIGHT,
BUT STILL--
- HUH?
EITA, WHAT IS THAT?
- MARGERY, DO YOU REALLY
WANNA GO IN THERE?
- BET YOUR ASS I DO.
THIS LOOKS LIKE THE PERFECT
PLACE TO BEAT THE HEAT.
- HEY, LET'S COME BACK
TOMORROW.
TODAY ISN'T THE BEST DAY
FOR VISITING THE PARK.
- HMM?
- HMM.
- SOMETHING WRONG?
- THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
IS HERE.
- UH, THE CHANTER OF--
THAT WOMAN'S HERE?
- MMM.
I DON'T SENSE ANY ANGER IN HER.
- ( chuckling )
- WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
- YOU TWO ARE.
THESE TOUGH FLAME HAZES
SHOWING UP AT THE POOL
JUST TO RELAX AND HAVE FUN.
IT'S KIND OF AMUSING
IN A WAY.
SHANA, STOP IT!
- SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
SHUT UP!
- I'M GOING TO THE FOOD STAND!
- OKAY.
- LOOK WHERE WE ARE.
- WE DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE.
ONCE SHE WANTS SOMETHING,
THAT'S IT.
BUT THIS IS A RISK.
WHAT IF WE RUN INTO OGA-CHAN
AND THE OTHERS?
- COME ON, WE'LL BE OKAY.
I MEAN, LOOK AT
ALL THE PEOPLE HERE.
CHANCES ARE
WE'LL NEVER EVEN SEE THEM.
- ( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
- OGA-CHAN!
- YOU BETTER HAVE AN EXCUSE.
- UM, WE CAN EXPLAIN THIS.
- I ONLY ASKED THEM TO GO
AND BUY ME ONE LOUSY DRINK.
WHAT IS TAKING
THOSE TWO SO LONG?
- ( Marco laughing )
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
THEY FINALLY HAD ENOUGH
OF THE BOTTOMLESS BOOZEHOUND.
OW!
- Ogata:
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
YOU TURNED DOWN MY INVITATION
TO COME,
AND THEN YOU SHOW UP ANYWAY?
DID YOU TWO COME HERE
WITH SOMEONE ELSE?
- WHAT'S GOING ON BACK THERE?
- DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT SURE, BUT IT SOUNDS
LIKE A CASE OF JEALOUSY TO ME.
- Tanaka: WELL, YOU SEE--
- TELL ME!
- ( gasps )
- SO YOU REALLY DID COME HERE
JUST TO RELAX BY THE POOL?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE GETTING
INTO A TUSSLE WITH YOU.
FIND SOMEONE ELSE TO FIGHT.
( moans, exhales )
ALL THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
WANTS RIGHT NOW
IS TO LIE BY THE POOL
WITH A COOL DRINK.
- Alastor: WELL, I SEE HER DAYS
AS A FLAME HAZE ARE OVER.
- HMM.
NOT THAT IT MATTERS TO US
WHAT SHE WANTS TO DO.
- THEN YOU SAID
YOU WEREN'T COMING YESTERDAY
BECAUSE YOU WANTED
TO SURPRISE US?
- YEAH, THAT'S IT.
WE THOUGHT IF WE JUST SAID YES,
EVERYONE WOULDN'T BE THAT
APPRECIATIVE OF OUR PRESENCE.
RIGHT, SATO?
- YEAH.
WELL, WE THOUGHT WE'D SHOW UP
SUDDENLY
AND MAKE THINGS INTERESTING
FOR YOU.  RIGHT, TANAKA?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- HUH.
AND YOU NEVER BOTHERED
TO TELL ME.
- LIKE I SAID,
I'M REAL SORRY.
- HMM.
THEN YOU WON'T MIND HELPING US
IN THE WATER FIGHT!
- WATER FIGHT?
- GOT THAT? THE PERSON AT THE
OTHER END WILL BE YOUR PARTNER.
THE ODD MAN OUT
WILL CHEER THEM ON, OKAY?
- WHAT DO WE DO? BIG SISTER
IS STILL WAITING FOR US.
- WHAT OTHER CHOICE
DO WE HAVE?
BETTER TO PLAY ALONG THAN TO
HAVE THEM FIND OUT ABOUT HER.
- OKAY, I'M LETTING GO.
- ( both chuckling )
- IT'S THE MOMENT
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR,
A TRADITION
HERE AT MISAKI WATERLAND--
THE COUPLE'S WATER BATTLE
COMPETITION. IT'S PRETTY SIMPLE.
THE PERSON WITH THE MOST
HEADBANDS AT THE END
WINS THE CONTEST.
HOWEVER, IF YOU SHOULD
LOSE YOUR OWN HEADBAND--
- WHERE'S IKE? HE SAID HE WAS
JUST GOING TO THE BATHROOM.
- I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING
TO CHEER ALL OF US ON.
- THE TEAM WITH THE MOST
HEADBANDS AT THE END
OF REGULATION TIME
WILL RECEIVE A PRIZE PACKAGE
INCLUDING DINNER
AT THE CITY'S
FINEST RESTAURANT.
- DINNER WITH SAKAI
AT A RESTAURANT.
DINNER WITH SAKAI AT A
RESTAURANT WITH A NIGHT VIEW.
- WIN AND YOU GET ALL THE
MELON BREAD YOU CAN EAT.
WIN AND YOU GET ALL
THE MELON BREAD YOU CAN EAT!
- UNDERSTAND, TANAKA?
THIS ALL DEPENDS ON YOU
KEEPING YOUR LEGS MOVING.
- YEAH, I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- YOSHIDA,
LET'S DO OUR BEST, 'KAY?
- YEAH, OKAY!
- DON'T BE SO TENSE.
TRY RELAXING A BIT MORE.
- I'LL TRY.
- ( grunts )
- Announcer:
IT'S FRANTIC!  IT'S FUN!
IT'S THE COUPLE'S
WATER BATTLE!
YOU ONLY HAVE THREE MINUTES.
AND READY!
- ( blowing )
- THERE'S NO SENSE
JUMPING ON EACH OTHER.
LET'S TARGET OTHER TEAMS FIRST.
- OKAY.
GOOD IDEA!
- ( grunting )
- OH, NO!
- COME TO MAMA!
- ( gasping )
- ( both screaming )
- WHAT'S THIS?
HEY, LOOK!
- KAZUMI'S PRETTY GOOD
AT THIS GAME.
HOWEVER...
- ( both grunting )
- ( girls shout )
- YOU'VE GOTTA KEEP YOUR WITS
ABOUT YOU IN THIS KINDA FIGHT.
- THEY'RE A STRONG TEAM,
BUT THEY DON'T SEEM TO BE USING
THEIR HEADS MUCH.
- ( all grunting )
- UH-HUH!
WHO'S NEXT?
- HIRAI'S PRETTY AWESOME.
- SATO'S RUNNING HIS LEGS OFF.
- LET'S MAKE SURE WE STAY
FAR AWAY FROM THAT TEAM.
- YOU BETCHA.
- FOLKS!
THERE ISN'T THAT MUCH TIME LEFT,
AND THERE AREN'T THAT MANY
COUPLES LEFT WITH HEADBANDS.
- HEY, YOSHIDA, WE'RE LUCKY
TO HAVE MADE IT THIS FAR.
LET'S JUST WAIT FOR THE TIME
TO RUN OUT.
WE WON'T WIN, BUT I'M SURE WE'LL
GET SOMETHING FOR SURVIVING.
- YEAH, SURE.
I'M JUST HAPPY
I WAS ABLE
TO SPEND THIS MUCH TIME
ALONE WITH HIM.
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME.
- UH, YOSHIDA,
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- HUH?  NO!
EVERYTHING'S JUST PERFECT!
- Announcer: LOOK, THE HIRAI
TEAM IS ON THE MOVE!
- YUJI!
- OH, CRAP!
WE'D BETTER MAKE A RUN FOR IT.
- OKAY.
- STOP!
- WHAT ARE THOSE GUYS DOING?
- YUJI!
- YEAH.
- WHY ARE YOU RUNNING?
- WHY ARE YOU CHASING US?
YOU'VE ALREADY WON.
LEAVE OUR HEADBAND ALONE!
- SHUT UP!
SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
THIS IS STILL PART
OF THE TRAINING!
- YOU'RE TALKIN' CRAZY!
- I AM NOT TALKING CRAZY!
- THEY SEEM COMFORTABLE
WITH EACH OTHER.  MUST BE NICE.
- YOSHIDA, BEND DOWN.
SHE'S RIGHT THERE.
- UH?
- LOOK, PICK UP THE PACE,
WILL YA?
- THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
- YUJI, STOP!
- I'M NOT STOPPING!
- IS SHE ANGRY
BECAUSE SAKAI AND I
ARE SPENDING SO MUCH TIME
TOGETHER?
BUT WHY WOULD SHE CARE?
- FASTER!  FASTER!
- I'M ABOUT DONE.
- STAND STILL, YUJI!
- AAH!  SHE'S ON OUR TAIL.
DON'T STOP!
- HA!  GOTCHA!
YOU'RE MINE!
AAH!
- ( whistle blows )
- AND TIME'S UP!
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT
A SURPRISE WINNER, FOLKS!
THE OKADA TEAM!
- ( both cheering )
- MR. OKADA WAS IN THE CONTEST?
- YOU KNOW, SHOULD THAT COUNT?
- I WONDER IF THAT'S HIS WIFE.
- Yuji: HEY, WHY DID YOU
HAVE TO COME AFTER US?
- YOUR FAULT.
- MY FAULT?  WHY IS THAT?
- SHUT UP!
SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
- YOU KNOW, SHANA,
YOU'RE ALWAYS SAYING...
- YOUNG MAN, HAVE A SIP?
OH, YEAH, YOU'RE TOO YOUNG
TO HAVE A DRINK.
SUCKS TO BE YOU.
- WHO IS THIS WOMAN ANYWAY?
IT'S PRETTY LATE.
I WONDER HOW EVERYONE'S DOING.
- ( yawning )
- WE'RE SORRY,
BUT WE COULDN'T HELP IT.
WE DIDN'T MEAN
TO LEAVE YOU ALONE.
- AH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WHAT WAS I USING FOR A PILLOW?
MY NECK HURTS.
- I'D SAY THAT WAS
A PRETTY FUN DAY, ALL IN ALL.
WELL, TOMORROW'S MONDAY.
I'LL SEE YOU AT SCHOOL.
- YEAH, TAKE IT EASY.
- SEE YA TOMORROW!
- SO WHY DID YOU COME AFTER ME?
- SHUT UP!
- WHY WON'T YOU TELL ME?
SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: IT'S HARD TO TELL OTHERS
HOW YOU FEEL.
SHANA GOES INTO BATTLE ALONE,
HER EARS RINGING
WITH THE SCREAMS OF RINNE.
IN THE MEANTIME, MORE DENIZENS
APPEAR IN THE CITY.
NEXT EPISODE...