- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
Yuji: THE BATTLE WAS OVER.
IN THE AFTERMATH,
QUESTIONS REMAINED.
WHAT HAD THE DENIZEN,
KNOWN AS THE PROFESSOR,
REALLY BEEN TRYING
TO ACCOMPLISH?
AND THEN, THERE
WAS ANOTHER MATTER.
- Yoshida: SAKAI,
YOU'RE SO WARM.
NO, SAKAI, YOU'RE HUMAN.
- EVEN AFTER SHE
FOUND OUT WHAT I WAS,
YOSHIDA REVEALED HER
TRUE FEELINGS FOR ME.
AND THEN, THERE WAS SHANA.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT SEEMS TO BE
BOTHERING YOU?
- WIRHELMINA.
- IT DOESN'T REALLY LOOK
LIKE YOU'VE BEEN LIVING
IN THIS APARTMENT.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- Tiamat: CLEAN-UP REQUIRED.
- ( humming )
- UM, WIRHELMINA, HOW LONG
DO YOU INTEND TO STAY HERE?
- Tiamat: DURATION UNDETERMINED.
- Wirhelmina: UNTIL I'VE DONE
WHAT I CAME TO DO, INDEED.
- Alastor: WHICH IS?
- INDEED, THERE IS
A MYSTES IN THIS CITY,
AND IT CONTAINS
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- ( gasps )
- Yuji: IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE.
SO MUCH HAS HAPPENED, AND
ALL OF IT JUST LAST NIGHT.
- ( dog barks )
- HEY, YOSHIDA.
- HI THERE, SAKAI.
HOW'S IT GOIN'?
- ABOUT YESTERDAY,
I'M REALLY SORRY.
WE GOT YOU INVOLVED
IN A BUNCH OF STUFF.
- YOU DON'T HAVE
TO APOLOGIZE, SAKAI.
ACTUALLY, I'M HAPPY ABOUT IT.
BECAUSE OF WHAT HAPPENED, YOU
AND I GOT A LITTLE CLOSER.
IT HELPED ME TELL YOU
HOW I REALLY FEEL.
- UM, WELL THAT'S, THAT'S
NICE. THANK YOU, YOSHIDA.
- IT'S, IT'S ALRIGHT.
IT'S JUST THAT...
- Yuji: I'M GLAD YOSHIDA
TOLD ME HOW SHE FEELS.
I FEEL PRETTY GOOD ABOUT IT.
BUT THE ONLY THING
KEEPING ME ALIVE RIGHT NOW
IS THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- SAKAI? IS THERE
SOMETHING WRONG?
- UH-UH. NOPE, NOTHIN'S WRONG.
- SO THIS IS THE HOUSE WHERE
THE MYSTES WITH
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
CURRENTLY RESIDES?
- Tiamat: CONCEALED.
- YEAH. UH, WIRHELMINA,
WE SHOULD GO BACK.
BECAUSE THERE'S STILL SOME
CLEANING TO DO,
AND BESIDES, I WANNA TALK
ABOUT SOME STUFF.
- THIS MORNING AND NOW THIS?
UNCHARACTERISTIC BEHAVIOR
FOR A FLAME HAZE, INDEED.
- Chigusa: AH, SHANA-CHAN!
- SHANA?
- SO, YOU'RE NOT SPENDING
TIME WITH YU-CHAN TODAY?
HE SAID HE WAS STEPPING
OUT FOR A MINUTE,
AND THEN HE JUST
RAN OFF SOMEWHERE.
- HE'S NOT HERE.
- AND WHO IS YOUR FRIEND HERE?
- WELL, THIS IS...
- MY, MY! SO YOU'RE THE MISS
CARMEL I'VE HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT.
I SHOULD HAVE INTRODUCED
MYSELF PROPERLY.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER. THANK YOU
FOR TAKING CARE OF HER.
- I'M GLAD WE COULD MEET.
SHANA-CHAN'S TOLD ME
SO MUCH ABOUT YOU.
I UNDERSTAND YOU WERE THE
ONE WHO LOOKED AFTER HER
WHEN SHE WAS YOUNG.
- ISN'T THAT
RIGHT, SHANA-CHAN?
- UH, YEAH.
- PLEASE, MADAME.
- MADAME SOUNDS SO
FORMAL, WHAT IS IT?
- YOU KEEP ADDRESSING
HER BY THAT NAME,
BUT I'D INDEED LIKE YOU
TO STOP CALLING HER THAT.
- WIRHELMINA!
- I SEE, PLEASE EXCUSE ME THEN.
MR. ALASTOR TOLD ME THAT SHE
PREFERRED TO BE CALLED THAT,
SO NATURALLY I ASSUMED
THAT YOU ALSO LIKED TO
CALL HER THAT, MS. CARMEL.
- THINGS ARE INDEED
STARTING TO BECOME CLEAR.
THE FLAMING-HAIRED BLAZING-EYED
HUNTER HAS BECOME
RUSTY BECAUSE OF THIS WOMAN.
- SO, WHERE ARE YOU STAYING,
MS. CARMEL? AT YUKARI'S PLACE?
- YES, MADAME.
I PLAN ON TAKING UP
RESIDENCE IN YOUR CITY
FOR SOME TIME INDEED.
I HOPE YOU'LL UNDERSTAND IF
WHILE I'M HERE,
NATURALLY I WILL BE
TAKING CARE OF HER.
INDEED, I'M NOT LETTING THIS
WOMAN INFLUENCE HER ANY LONGER.
- WHY THAT'S WONDERFUL!
I'D LIKE TO THINK WE'VE BEEN
ABLE TO PROVIDE YUKARI
WITH SUPPORT AND COMFORT,
SO SHE WOULDN'T FEEL
SO LONELY ON HER OWN.
NEVERTHELESS, NOTHING CAN TAKE
THE PLACE OF FAMILY, NOW CAN IT?
THAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT THING.
- FAMILY.
- EXCUSE ME, I'M NOT
RELATED TO HER BY BLOOD.
I MERELY HELPED RAISE HER,
NOTHING MORE INDEED.
- OH, YOU DON'T SAY.
YUKARI-CHAN, IS THAT
NOTHING TO YOU?
- MMM-MMM.
- WHETHER OR NOT YOU'RE RELATED
BY BLOOD IS VERY A MINOR DETAIL
TO A FAMILY THAT LIVES TOGETHER.
- Wirhelmina: THIS WOMAN IS
INDEED DETESTABLE.
- BE CAREFUL.
- I KNOW.
- ( grunts )
- Tanaka: 35 CENTIMETRES!
A NEW RECORD!
- ( panting )
- OKAY. MY TURN.
- WE ARE GONNA LIFT THIS
THING, NO MATTER WHAT!
- YEAH, UNLESS
WE ACCOMPLISH THIS,
WE'RE NOT GONNA BE ANY
HELP WHEN IT COUNTS.
- ( grunts )
- Marco: THEY'RE REALLY
GOING FOR IT.
PROBABLY BECAUSE
OF ALL THE ATTENTION
THAT MYSTES BOY IS GETTING.
- IS THAT FROM HIM?
- YES.
BUT JUST AFTER KHAMSIN
GAVE IT TO ME,
HE SAID SOMETHING
THAT GAVE ME THE CREEPS.
- THAT REMINDS ME.
FOR HELPING WITH THE TUNING,
I HAVE AN AMULET FOR YOU.
- CAN I REALLY HAVE THIS?
- A TOKEN OF OUR APPRECIATION.
BY THE WAY, I MUST WARN
YOU TWO ABOUT SOMETHING.
WE'RE STILL NOT SURE
WHAT THE PROFESSOR WAS AFTER,
BUT WE HEAR THERE'S A LOT OF
SIGNIFICANT MOVEMENT OUT THERE
CONCERNING THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD.
- HMM? THE ONE INSIDE ME?
- Khamsin: IT WOULD BE WISE
TO EXERCISE CAUTION.
- MOVEMENT, HE SAID. RIGHT.
- SAKAI, YOU AND YUKARI HAVE
BEEN FIGHTING THIS BATTLE
BY YOURSELVES FOR A WHILE NOW.
- I HAD NO IDEA ABOUT THIS.
- WELL, YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE.
THE VAST MAJORITY OF
PEOPLE LIVE THEIR LIVES
WITHOUT KNOWING ANY OF THIS.
AND IF POSSIBLE, THEY'RE
BETTER OFF THAT WAY.
- Yoshida: SAKAI...
- Yuji: I'VE NEVER GIVEN IT
MUCH THOUGHT BEFORE,
BUT I REALLY LOVE THIS CITY.
IT'S THE PLACE WHERE
MY MOM, YOSHIDA,
AND ALL MY FRIENDS LIVE.
THEY'RE THE REASONS I
WANNA PROTECT IT SO DESPERATELY.
I NEVER WANT MY CITY, OR
THE PEOPLE WHO LIVE IN IT,
TO GET INVOLVED IN THE KIND
OF MESS WE HAD YESTERDAY.
UM, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I'M SORRY, BUT
FOR A SECOND THERE,
I HAD THE FEELING YOU'RE ABOUT
TO GO VERY FAR AWAY SOON.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- IT'S FOR THE
TRADITIONAL BONFIRE.
- THAT'S RIGHT! THEY HAVE A
BIG FIRE EVERY YEAR.
I THOUGHT ALL THOSE ORNAMENTS
HAD BEEN TRANSFORMED
INTO RINNES.
HUH?
- SAKAI, IS THERE SOMETHING
WRONG THERE?
- UH, SORRY.
IT'S NOTHING, LET'S GO.
IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT,
BUT I SHOULD CHECK WITH
SHANA, JUST IN CASE.
FIND OUT IF THAT THING'S SAFE.
- I NEVER IMAGINED YOU'D BE
STAYING IN THE SAME HOUSE
WHERE THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD IS.
- Tiamat: UNFORSEEN.
- Wirhelmina: AND YOU WERE WITH
HER, FLAME OF THE HEAVENS.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
- Alastor: Hmm.
- SO WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU
MEAN WHEN YOU SAY, "HMM?"
- Tiamat: DUTIES NEGLECTED.
- ( Alastor clears throat )
- I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY
TROUBLE WITH US STAYING HERE.
YUJI'S BEEN, WHAT I MEAN TO
SAY IS THE MYSTES HAS BEEN
HELPFUL IN OUR BATTLES.
- Alastor: ALTHOUGH
HE'S STILL INEXPERIENCED
AND LACKS
DETERMINATION AT TIMES.
- PLEASE TELL ME, WIRHELMINA,
WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU PLANNING
ON DOING WITH THE MYSTES?
- I HEARD THAT THOUSAND
CHANGES WAS HERE.
- YES, SYDONAY.
- Alastor: YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT THE BALL MASQUE.
- YES, INDEED, FOR IT IS
THEY WHO ARE MAKING
THREATENING MOVES AGAINST
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- Yuji: I'M HOME!
- ( gasps )
- Yuji: MOM, SHANA'S
HERE, ISN'T SHE?
HEY, SHANA, THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANNA TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
WHA...
- YU-CHAN, INTRODUCE
YOURSELF PLEASE.
THIS IS WIRHELMINA CARMEL, THE
PERSON WHO RAISED YUKARI-CHAN,
FROM WHEN SHE WAS JUST A CHILD.
- WHO RAISED HER?
- Yoshida: EKATERINA!
YOU CAN'T RUN
INTO PEOPLE'S YARDS!
- Wirhelmina: SO THIS IS INDEED
WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT.
- ( Shana sobs )
- SHANA.
- SHANA-CHAN!
- IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
MADAME,
I'LL HANDLE THINGS
FROM THIS POINT ON.
- SURE.
- WE MUST SEVER ALL
SOURCES OF DISTRACTION.
- Tanaka: SO, OUR PERSONAL
BEST IS 48 CENTIMETRES.
- Sato: A LONG WAY TO GO
BEFORE WE CAN SWING IT AROUND.
BUT A DEFINITE IMPROVEMENT.
- LET'S GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
- YEAH.
BIG SISTER, WHAT WOULD
YOU LIKE FOR DINNER?
WE'RE THINKING WE'D LIKE
SOMETHING TO BOOST
OUR ENERGY LEVEL.
THAT'S STRANGE. IS
SHE SLEEPING AGAIN?
- Tanaka: MARGERY?
- Sato: MARGERY!
- Tanka: BIG SISTER!
- Sato: MARGERY?
- Sato: MARGERY!
- HELLO? COME IN, BIG SISTER.
WOULD YOU AT LEAST
SAY SOMETHING?
- Tanka: BIG SISTER!
- Sato: TANAKA!
- Marco: ARE YOU LEAVING
THAT SWORD BEHIND?
- Margery: YEAH, BESIDES, IT
NEVER REALLY SUITED ME.
IT'S TOO UNSTABLE.
- Marco: YOU ARE SO RIGHT.
GIVING AN UNSTABLE WEAPON
TO SOMEONE AS UNSTABLE
AS YOU IS...
- ( Marco screams )
- SHUT UP, STUPID MARCO.
- Marco: THIS MAY BE A
SILLY QUESTION,
BUT ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
THE BALL MASQUE IS ON
THE MOVE, YOU KNOW.
- Margery: THAT'S WHY WE NEED TO
BE ONE STEP AHEAD OF THEM.
AND THERE ARE SOME THINGS WE
HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF, TOO.
- Marco: YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- WE STAYED HERE LONGER
THAN WE SHOULD HAVE.
- Marco: YEAH, YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
- GOOD LUCK TO YOU, MISAKI CITY.
- Marco: AND GOOD LUCK TO OUR
BELOVED FOLLOWERS AS WELL.
- Tanaka: DOES THIS SEEM
RIGHT TO YOU?
- Sato: HOW COULD THEY LEAVE
WITHOUT SAYING ANYTHING?
- IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT.
- ( grunts )
- Sato: HOW COULD YOU?
DAMMIT... DAMMIT... DAMMIT.
- Wirhelmina: SO THAT
WAS THE MYSTES WITH
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
WE MUST ACT UPON
THIS IMMEDIATELY.
INDEED WE MUST GO AS
SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- ACT UPON THIS?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- Wirhelmina: BALL MASQUE
HAS ALWAYS DESIRED
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD,
AND NOW THOUSAND CHANGES
HAS FOUND IT.
THEREFORE, AS FLAME HAZES,
IT IS OUR DUTY TO THWART THEM
IN THEIR NEFARIOUS PLAN
WITH THE SINGLE MOST EFFECTIVE
METHOD AS POSSIBLE, INDEED.
IN OTHER WORDS,
WE MUST DESTROY
THE MYSTES AND TRANSFER
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
TO A DIFFERENT LOCATION.
- Tiamat: RANDOM TRANSFER.
- WAIT! WIRHELMINA!
BUT THAT MEANS...
- INDEED, AS FLAME HAZES,
THIS IS THE ONLY STEP WE
CAN TAKE TO RESOLVE THIS.
- Yuji: I NEVER REALIZED
HOW BIG MISAKI CITY IS.
THAT'S MY HOUSE, AND THIS
IS WHERE THE SCHOOL IS,
AND THIS IS IKE'S HOUSE, HERE.
THIS IS THE SHOPPING DISTRICT
WHERE I FIRST MET SHANA.
AND HERE'S THE DEPARTMENT
STORE WHERE WE FOUGHT FRIAGNE.
THIS IS THE MUSEUM
WHERE WE BEAT MARGERY.
THIS IS MISAKI BRIDGE,
WHERE I FACED THAT DENIZEN.
AND THE RIVERBED
WHERE WE WERE LAST NIGHT.
ALL OVER THE CITY,
IN A SHORT TIME.
I'M LEAVING ALL THIS.
LEAVING TO HELP SHANA
FIGHT DENIZENS.
LEAVING SO THAT MISAKI
CITY DOESN'T BECOME INVOLVED
IN THE STRUGGLE.
I'M A MYSTES, AND THAT'S
THE ROAD I HAVE TO WALK
FROM NOW ON.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, SHANA?
- Wirhelmina: ON A STROLL
AT THIS LATE HOUR?
YOU'VE INDEED SAVED ME THE
TROUBLE OF DRAWING YOU OUT.
- UH...
- PREPARE YOURSELF, MYSTES
I MUST DESTROY YOU.
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- YOU WON'T SUFFER LONG.
- Tiamat: SINGLE SHOT KILL.
- Wirhelmina: INDEED, IT'S NO
USE CALLING FOR HELP.
THE FLAME-HAIRED BLAZING-EYED
HUNTER FULLY SUPPORTS
MY DECISION TO DESTROY YOU.
- ( gasps )
- SHANA? SHANA SUPPORTS THIS?
- I AM A FLAME HAZE. MY
MISSION IS TO PRESERVE
THE BALANCE OF THE WORLD.
( sobs ) I AM A FLAME HAZE,
THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
- THIS IS THE END, INDEED.
- Tiamat: FINAL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE DUTY
OF A FLAME HAZE,
AND THE FEELINGS OF A GIRL.
SHANA FINDS HERSELF CONFLICTED
OVER YUJI,
WHO IS STILL SET ON
LEAVING THE CITY BEHIND.
NEXT EPISODE,
"DIVERGING FEELINGS."