- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- YES, BUT IT'S STILL BETTER
THAN WAITING FOR THE END TO COME
AND THEN BEING FORGOTTEN.
I THINK MY EXISTENCE,
MY MEMORY,
IS A PART OF IKE
AND THE OTHERS NOW.
AND THEN THERE'S YOU.
YOU WON'T FORGET ME.
- Shana: YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT IT WON'T MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE
IN THE END.
- Yuji: SHE WAS GOING
TO REMEMBER ME,
AND AT THE TIME I THOUGHT
THAT WAS ENOUGH.
BUT THERE WAS SO MUCH
I DIDN'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING.
- ( bird squawking )
- I WONDER WHERE SHE WENT.
MMM.
- ( leaves rustling )
- HUH?
OH NO, SHANA!
- STAY BACK!
- WHAT-- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
- YOU'RE HURT.
- IT'S YOUR FAULT.
- ( gasps )
I'LL GET SOMETHING
FOR YOU TO CHANGE INTO.
COME INTO THE HOUSE.
SHANA.
- YOU'RE NOTHING TO ME.
JUST A TORCH.
- Friagne:
SO I WASN'T IMAGINING THINGS.
- ( flames whooshing out )
- SOMEONE OUT THERE
IS REMOVING ALL OF THE TORCHES
I SO CAREFULLY PLACED.
- IS IT HER?
- NO.  THIS ISN'T THE WORK
OF A FLAME HAZE.
IF THEY WANTED TO LURE ME
INTO THE OPEN,
THEY WOULD ERASE MORE
THAN A SINGLE TORCH AT A TIME.
- MMM.
- BESIDES, I DON'T THINK
THEY EVEN KNOW
THAT I NEED THE TORCHES.
THEY DON'T KNOW
THAT I PLAN ON USING THEM.
- OH, MASTER.
( crying )
- THERE, THERE, MARIANNE.
NO MATTER WHO THEY ARE,
I WON'T LET THEM GET AWAY
WITH THEIR TAMPERING.
THAT I PROMISE.
- Yuji: BYE, MOM!
HMM.
- I CAN DO IT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I CAN SAY IT.
I CAN DO IT.  IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- HEY, YOSHIDA,
GOOD MORNING.
- HUH?
HI, GOOD MORNING, IKE.
- SO, WHAT'S UP?
- OH, NOTHING.
WHERE'S SAKAI?
- UM, I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM YET.
- OH.
- WHY?  DO YOU WANT
TO SPEAK TO HIM?
- NO!
I MEAN, YES, BUT...
MY DAD GAVE ME
THESE TWO FREE TICKETS.
OR MAYBE EVEN A MOVIE,
THAT WOULD BE OKAY.
BUT I THOUGHT
THIS WOULD BE NICE TOO.
AND SO I THOUGHT I'D JUST--
- GOOD MORNING!
- GOOD MORNING TO YOU TOO.
- AH, SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
- PARDON ME?
- SO GOT ANYTHING LINED UP
AFTER SCHOOL?
- AFTER SCHOOL?
NOTHING IN PARTICULAR.
- AH, EXCELLENT.
HEY, YOSHIDA,
WHAT ABOUT SAKAI HERE?
- WHAT?
- YOU WERE TELLING ME ABOUT
THAT PERSON WHO CANCELED
AND HOW YOU NEED SOMEONE
TO GO WITH.
- ME?
UM, WELL, I HAVE TWO TICKETS
TO THE ART EXHIBITION TODAY.
AND I THOUGHT IF YOU WEREN'T
DOING ANYTHING AFTER SCHOOL...
- TWO TICKETS?
- ( chuckles )
- WITH ME?
- MMM.
- ( horns honking )
- HMM.
CLASS HAS ALREADY STARTED.
WHAT A DRAG.
- SO YOU WANNA SKIP OUT?
- FOR SURE.
UH, WHAT'S WRONG?
- JUST OUR LUCK,
WE HAD TO RUN INTO THEM.
OH!
- THAT WAS QUITE A BEATING
SHE TOOK.
I DON'T THINK WE'LL SEE
THE BLAZING-EYED LITTLE BRAT
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
- Marco: YEAH, NOW IF WE
CAN JUST FIND OUR MAIN DISH,
THE CORPSE COLLECTOR,
WE'LL CHEW HIM UP
AND SPIT HIM OUT!
( laughs )
- SAME PLAN AS ALWAYS.
WE NEED TO FIND SOMEONE
WHO KNOWS THE CITY
AND CAN SHOW US AROUND.
- Marco: AND IT WOULDN'T HURT
IF THEY WERE YOUNG
AND GOOD LOOKING, EH?
- THAT'S ENOUGH, STUPID MARCO.
- ( grunting )
( both grunt )
- THESE TWO WILL DO JUST FINE.
- Marco: OKAY OKAY!
AREN'T THEY A BIT TOO YOUNG
FOR YOUR LIKING, THOUGH?
- GET BACK HERE!
- WE GOT HIM NOW.
- LOOK AT THIS.
- HA!
- ( boys grunting,
protesting )
- HMM.
- I-- I DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU ARE, LADY,
BUT WE'LL HURT YOU
IF WE HAVE TO.
SO YOU BETTER
NOT GET IN OUR WAY.
- DON'T MAKE ME HURT YOU BOYS
AS WELL.
- YOU JUST SHUT UP.
LET'S GO, TANAKA.
YOU DEAF?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- MAY I CALL YOU "BIG SISTER"?
CAN I?
- Ike: SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "HUH"?
AFTER CLASSES, AFTER SCHOOL?
- OH, UH...
- AFTER ALL, YOU SAID
YOU WERE FREE,
AND IT WOULD BE A SHAME TO LET
THOSE TICKETS GO TO WASTE.
YOU SHOULD GO WITH HER.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'D BE GLAD TO GO WITH YOU.
- Alastor: SHOULDN'T YOU BE
A LITTLE CLOSER TO THE MYSTES?
- ( humming )
- Marco:
AND THAT'S WHY THE TWO OF YOU
ARE GONNA HELP US LOOK
FOR THE DENIZEN IN THIS CITY.
( laughing )
- UNDERSTAND?
- Both: MM-HMM.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- SO, UM, BIG SISTER?
WHAT EXACTLY
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
- LET'S SEE, FOR NOW,
JUST ANSWER ANY QUESTIONS I ASK.
YOU BOYS ARE
FROM AROUND HERE, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- WATCH IT, KID.
- YES, MA'AM.
- HAVE THERE BEEN ANY MAJOR
DISTURBANCES OR ACCIDENTS?
ANYTHING OUT OF THE ORDINARY?
- HMM, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD BUY
A NEWSPAPER?
I DON'T READ THE PAPER.
BUT I HEARD ABOUT SOME TRAFFIC
ACCIDENTS, BUT NOTHING ELSE.
- Both: HMM.
- WELL.
THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE
ABOUT THIS CITY.
- ( flames whooshing out )
- PLEASE STAY HERE, MARIANNE.
- MASTER?
- HMM, I FOUND YOU.
- Alastor:
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
- WHY WHAT?
- Alastor: WHY YOU LOST
TO THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- ( inaudible )
- THAT'S IT?
JUST ONE LITTLE ROBBERY?
THERE HASN'T BEEN ANYTHING
ELSE UNUSUAL?
- NO, NOTHING.
- THEN LET'S FOCUS
ON THOSE TORCHES
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT.
WHERE WOULD WE FIND A LARGE
GROUP OF THEM CONGREGATING?
- Both: UH...
- THEN WHAT ABOUT A SPOT
WHERE A LOT OF PEOPLE
TEND TO GATHER?
- LET'S SEE...
THERE'S ALWAYS A BIG CROWD
AT THE STATION.
- OKAY, WE'LL START
WITH THE BUILDING
AND THEN DO A THOROUGH SEARCH
OF THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
- WHAT'S UP?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- A PALE WHITE FLAME.
- Marco:
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
- THE HUNTER, FRIAGNE.
- UH...
- YOU BOYS CHILL.
JUST WAIT HERE FOR A BIT.
- THAT'S STRANGE.
THE CULPRIT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
SOMEWHERE AROUND HERE.
- I DIDN'T EXPECT
TO RUN INTO HIM.
QUITE A BIG CATCH,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- Marco: YEAH, IT'S LIKE CHASING
A MINNOW AND FINDING A WHALE.
( laughing )
- A PERFECT CHANCE
TO KILL HIM.  AGREED?
- Marco: AGREED.  I THINK
THAT'S A FANTASTIC IDEA.
MARGERY DAW,
MY FANGS OF DESTRUCTION!
- I CAN SENSE IT.
THERE'S A FLAME HAZE NEAR.
- THE HUNTER
IS ON THE MOVE AGAIN.
- Alastor: LEAVE HIM BE.
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
IS HEADING THAT WAY NOW.
- BUT--
- Alastor: IT'S DANGEROUS.
YOU'RE TOO DISTRACTED.
THERE ARE OTHER THINGS
WE MUST DO IN THE MEANTIME.
- WOW, THIS ONE'S BEAUTIFUL.
- YEAH, IT SURE IS.
THERE'S A LOT MORE.
I HEAR THERE'S A STAINED-GLASS
DISPLAY IN THE BACK.
- REALLY?
LET'S GO SEE IT.
- OKAY, SOUNDS GOOD.
- HUH?
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- AH, SO YOU CAN TELL.
NOW I SEE.
YOU'RE A MYSTES.
HAVE NO FEAR.
I'M NOT GOING
TO DO ANYTHING WITH YOU.
- ( gasping )
- I DISLIKE DOING ANYTHING RASH,
ANYTHING THAT WOULD UPSET
THE BALANCE OF THE WORLD.
- AH.
- I THINK YOU AND I
SHOULD HAVE A TALK.
- DO YOU KNOW THIS PERSON?
- UH, I-- WELL, YEAH, SORT OF.
- Friagne: MARGERY DAW,
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
AND MARCOSIAS, THE CLAWS
AND FANGS OF VIOLATION.
- HUNTER FRIAGNE.
- SO YOU'RE THE NEW FLAME HAZE
IN TOWN.
SOMEHOW I DOUBT IT,
BUT ARE YOU THE ONES
WHO HAVE BEEN MEDDLING
IN MY AFFAIRS?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKIN' ABOUT.
I ONLY DECIDED TO KILL YOU
JUST NOW.
- I SEE THEN.
IT SEEMS THE ONE
WHO'S BEEN SO RUDELY
TAMPERING WITH
MY TORCHES HAS ALREADY LEFT.
- HMM?  HE WAS HERE?
- Marco: HOO-HOO!  SOUNDS LIKE
THE HUNTER'S AFTER HIM TOO.
- NEVER MIND. I REALLY DON'T
HAVE TIME TO PLAY AROUND
WITH A SIMPLE TOOL
FOR DESTRUCTION LIKE YOU.
BUT I GUESS THE SMART THING
WOULD BE TO KICK A STONE
OUT OF THE WAY
BEFORE I END UP
TRIPPING ON IT.
- I'LL TEACH YOU TO INTERFERE
WITH MY PREY!
- YOUR PREY?
- Marco:
EVEN IF YOU AREN'T READY,
WE'LL STILL RIP YOU APART!
( laughing )
- ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL, SAKAI?
HMM.
- LET ME INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM LAMIES,
THE CORPSE COLLECTOR.
AND, AS YOU'VE SURMISED,
I AM A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
- SO YOU'RE ONE OF THEM.
HUH?
ARE YOU THE ONE
WHO HURT SHANA?
- SHANA?
- SHE'S A FLAME HAZE,
OF COURSE.
- RELAX, I DID NO SUCH THING.
BUT FIRST OFF,
I INTRODUCED MYSELF.
PERHAPS YOU WOULD
RETURN THE FAVOR
AND TELL ME WHO YOU ARE,
MY YOUNG MYSTES FRIEND.
- MY NAME IS YUJI SAKAI.
- YOU SOUND QUITE CERTAIN.
YOU'VE RETAINED YOUR SANITY,
DESPITE LEARNING THE TRUE NATURE
OF THE SITUATION YOU'RE IN.
THAT'S QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
OR PERHAPS YOU'VE
SIMPLY GIVEN UP ON EVERYTHING.
- HUH?
- YOU MENTIONED SHANA
A MOMENT AGO.
IS THAT FLAME HAZE
OFTEN BY YOUR SIDE?
- I GAVE HER THE NAME SHANA.
SHE'S THE FLAME-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED ONE.
- SHE'S WHAT?
THEN I IMAGINE ALASTOR,
THE FLAME OF THE HEAVENS,
IS NEARBY.
- YOU MEAN YOU TWO KNOW
EACH OTHER?
- HMM, YES,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I SEE, THE FLAME-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
THEN I SHOULD BE ABLE TO AVOID
A MEANINGLESS FIGHT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN AVOID IT?
YOU'RE A CRIMSON DENIZEN.
- I DO NOT VICTIMIZE HUMANS.
I AM CALLED
THE CORPSE COLLECTOR
BECAUSE I PREY
SOLELY ON TORCHES THAT ARE WEAK,
LIKE THE ONE
YOU JUST SAW THERE,
ON THE VERGE
OF VANISHING ANYWAY.
IN FACT, THIS BODY
WAS BORROWED FROM A TORCH,
SO AS TO CONSERVE THE POWER
OF EXISTENCE.
- WHY WOULD YOU
WANT TO DO THAT?
- I HAVE MY REASONS.
- WHAT REASONS?
- I HAVE DEVELOPED
AN UNRESTRICTED
METHOD OF RESTORATION.
I'M IN THE PROCESS OF GATHERING
ENOUGH POWER OF EXISTENCE
TO PUT IT INTO EFFECT.
THAT IS MY PURPOSE IN LIFE.
I WANT TO SEE
THE INFINITE FUTURE
THAT LIES BEFORE US
WITH MY OWN EYES.
I WANT TO TOUCH IT
AND MAKE IT A CERTAINTY.
- THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE TARGETING TORCHES?
- ALTHOUGH I ONLY GATHER
THE WEAK ONES, YOU'RE A TORCH,
AND I UNDERSTAND HOW THIS
KNOWLEDGE MUST BOTHER YOU.
REST ASSURED,
MY STAY HERE WILL BE BRIEF.
I KEEP MOVING TO STAY AHEAD
OF THE HOUNDS,
AND THERE ARE OTHERS OUT THERE
WHO ARE NOT VERY PLEASED
WITH MY ACTIONS IN GENERAL.
- HUH?
- ( thunder rumbling )
- TIME TO GET
THIS PARTY STARTED!
STRIKE WITHOUT MERCY,
MARCOSIAS!
- Marco: WE'LL KILL HIM!
DESTROY HIM!
WE'LL TEAR HIM TO PIECES!
- I GET THE IMPRESSION
YOU KNOW
WHO'S BEEN DEVOURING
ALL OF MY TORCHES HERE.
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
WE'RE THE ONES HUNTING LAMIES.
THAT BASTARD IS OUR CATCH!
LET'S SEE YOU
GET AWAY FROM THOSE.
- LAMIES?
LAMIES THE CORPSE COLLECTOR?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT HIM
BECAUSE YOUR TIME IS UP!
- FLAME-REPELLING RING,
AZURE.
- WHAT?
- Marco: THAT'S NOT FAIR!
- COME BACK HERE!
- I'D LOVE TO PLAY SOME MORE,
BUT I JUST
DON'T HAVE THE TIME.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET AWAY
THAT EASILY!  AAH!
( gasps )
HE'S GONE.
DAMN THAT ASSHOLE!
DAMN ALL OF THEM.
- ARE YOU OKAY, BIG SISTER?
- I NEED A DRINK!
SHOW ME A QUIET PLACE
WITH A LOT OF ALCOHOL
WHERE I CAN DRINK MY FACE OFF
AND THEN PASS OUT!
- BUT WHERE ARE WE GONNA FIND--
OH.
( laughs )
- ( sighs )
HMM.
- Lamies: YOU'VE TOLD ME
WHAT I WANTED TO KNOW.
IT'S TIME I GOT GOING.
- UM...
- ASK YOUR QUESTION.
IT'S ONLY FAIR
I RETURN THE FAVOR
AND PROVIDE YOU
WITH WHAT YOU WANT TO KNOW.
- IT'S NOT REALLY A QUESTION.
IT'S JUST, YOU SEEM
TO BE LIVING YOUR LIFE
FOR ONE SINGLE OBJECTIVE.
I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHAT THAT MUST FEEL LIKE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO ANSWER THAT.
I'M GONNA GO NOW.
- ARE YOU BOTHERED BY THE FACT
THAT YOUR EXISTENCE
WILL SOON DISAPPEAR?
- AH.
EVERYONE I EVER KNEW
IS GOING TO FORGET I WAS HERE,
BUT SHANA'S THE ONE PERSON
WHO WILL REMEMBER
THAT I ACTUALLY LIVED.
AND THAT'S--
- YOUNG MAN, CAN YOU SAY
WITH COMPLETE CONFIDENCE
THAT YOU ARE
THE REAL YUJI SAKAI?
- HUH?
- YOU APPEAR TO BE NOTHING MORE
THAN A TORCH TO ME.
- YOU'RE NOTHING TO ME.
JUST A TORCH.
- LET ME REPHRASE THAT.
YOU SAID SHE WILL ALWAYS
REMEMBER THAT YOU LIVED.
BUT ARE YOU FINE WITH THAT?
IS THE PERSON
SHE'S GOING TO REMEMBER
THE PERSON YOU ARE NOW?
THERE'S A REASON
I DIDN'T PREY ON YOU.
IT'S BECAUSE THE FLAME
OF YOUR TORCH
STILL BURNS BRIGHTLY
WITHIN YOUR BODY.
LET ME GIVE YOU
SOME INFORMATION.
THIS CITY IS IN GRAVE DANGER
AND NO ONE EVEN KNOWS IT YET.
THE PERSON YOU ARE RIGHT NOW
WILL KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH THIS KNOWLEDGE.
FRIAGNE HAS SOMETHING TERRIBLE
IN MIND FOR THIS PLACE.
HE'S GOING TO WIPE IT OUT.
HE PLANS TO CONSUME
THE ENTIRE CITY.
- HMM?
WIPE OUT THE CITY?
- NOTHING WILL BE LEFT
WHEN HE IS DONE.
YOU AND EVERYTHING
YOU'VE EVER COME INTO
CONTACT WITH WILL BE GONE.
EVERYTHING WILL DISAPPEAR.
- ( gasps )
- Alastor: WHY ARE YOU
DISTANCING YOURSELF FROM HIM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- TWO FLAME HAZES
TO DEAL WITH,
AS WELL AS LAMIES
THE CORPSE COLLECTOR.
WE HAVE TO MOVE QUICKLY.
A LITTLE EARLIER
THAN I'D LIKE, MARIANNE,
BUT I THINK WE SHOULD
PUT THE PLAN IN MOTION.
- MASTER.
- HMM.
- I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT HIM?!
- Alastor: VERY WELL THEN.
- HE'S JUST A TORCH
THAT'S GONNA DISAPPEAR SOON.
- ( choir singing )
- Alastor: IT'S THAT MYSTES.
WE HAVE TO DESTROY
YUJI SAKAI.
- HUH?
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
Yuji: THE PLAN
TO CONSUME MISAKI COMMENCES.
BOTH THE CITY AND I
ARE IN GRAVE DANGER.
AND SHANA STRUGGLES
WITH HER INNER THOUGHTS
AS SHE CONFRONTS
THE DENIZEN, FRIAGNE.
NEXT EPISODE...