- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: SHANA AND I WERE
SPENDING A LOT OF TIME TOGETHER.
IN FACT, YOU COULD SAY
THINGS WERE ALMOST NORMAL.
THERE WERE TIMES WHEN I EVEN
FORGOT SHE WAS A FLAME HAZE,
AND WAS LOOKING MORE LIKE AN
ORDINARY GIRL TO ME EVERY DAY.
BUT THE TRAINING
THAT I HAD BEGUN
AFTER OUR BATTLE WITH FRIAGNE
WAS STILL ONGOING.
THOSE LESSONS BROUGHT ME
AND MY WANDERING THOUGHTS
BACK TO REALITY
PRETTY QUICKLY.
OW!
THEN I'D REMEMBER THAT IS A
STRONG, EXPERIENCED FLAME HAZE.
( grunting )
- YOU'RE LATE.
- SORRY.
- LET'S BEGIN,
SAME AS YESTERDAY.
SENSE THE KILL
AND AVOID THE ATTACK.
- YOU KNOW, THAT LOOKED GOOD
ON HER.
( grunting )
- STOP DAYDREAMING!
- I-- I WASN'T.
HEY!
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
KEEP HITTING ME SO HARD, SHANA.
- LOOK, IT'S POINTLESS
UNLESS I USE SOME FORCE.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE GETTING HIT,
YOU SHOULD LEARN TO AVOID IT.
- I'VE BEEN WORKING ON
KEEPING MY EYES OPEN.
ONE THING AT A TIME, OKAY?
- I CAN SEE THAT YOU'RE
STARTING TO FEEL THE KILL,
SO YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO SENSE A SIMPLE ATTACK.
IT'S LIKE PLAYING ROCK,
PAPER, SCISSORS
WHEN YOU ALREADY KNOW
WHAT YOUR OPPONENT WILL DO.
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT'S FUNNY?
- ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS.
YOU JUST LEARNED TO PLAY THAT
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
NOW YOU TALK LIKE AN EXPERT.
- SHUT UP!
SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
JUST STOP TALKING NONSENSE
DURING OUR TRAINING!
- ( grunting )
- HEY, HOW 'BOUT A WARNING?!
- ATTACKS ALWAYS COME
WITHOUT WARNING!
- BUT THAT'S TOO FAST!
AH!
- Alastor:
GOODNESS, YOU'RE CLUMSY.
- IT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE ALWAYS TALKING NONSENSE
THAT YOU END UP
IN THESE SITUATIONS.
- I ASKED YOU TO WAIT.
JEEZ, WOULD IT HAVE KILLED
YOU TO HOLD BACK FOR A BIT?
- AN ENEMY WILL
NOT WAIT FOR YOU.
- I KNOW THAT, BUT COME ON!
THIS IS A TRAINING SESSION,
REMEMBER?
- Alastor: EXCUSES
ARE FOR THE INCOMPETENT.
- ( grunting )
OH, BOY, MY PANTS.
- IF THAT WAS A DENIZEN,
YOU'D BE EATEN BY NOW.
- YEAH, WHATEVER.
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
I GOTTA GET READY FOR SCHOOL.
- YUJI.
- OH, WHERE'S YU-CHAN?
ARE YOU DONE ALREADY?
- I GUESS THE TRAINING
WASN'T GOING HIS WAY.
SO HE DECIDED TO END IT
EARLY.
- LOOKS LIKE HE GOT
KNOCKED AROUND A BIT.
- HE'S BEEN IN WORSE SHAPE
ON OTHER DAYS.
BUT IT'S NEVER BOTHERED HIM
LIKE THIS.
- MAYBE HE'S REALIZING HOW
AWKWARD HE LOOKS
COMPARED TO YOU.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN AWKWARD?
- YOU'RE A CUTE GIRL,
YOU WEAR A DRESS,
AND YOU'RE SMALLER THAN HE IS.
FROM A BOY'S POINT OF VIEW,
BEING BEATEN UP BY A GIRL
CAN BE PRETTY EMBARRASSING.
- WELL, I CAN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT I'M STRONGER THAN HE IS.
- BUT BOYS HAVE A TENDENCY
TO SHOW OFF IN FRONT OF OTHERS,
ESPECIALLY IN FRONT OF GIRLS
THEY'RE TRYING TO IMPRESS.
- YUJI'S TRYING TO IMPRESS ME?
I JUST WANT HIM TO BE...
- HAVE A NICE DAY,
YOU TWO!
- SO HERE'S THE PLAN--
TODAY AFTER SCHOOL,
I'M GONNA SET UP A SEAL SO WE
CAN PRACTICE SOME BIGGER MOVES.
- HUH.
IT'S YOUR CALL,
BUT SHOULD WE BE WORKING
ON COMPLICATED MOVES THIS SOON?
- IT'S PART OF YOUR TRAINING,
SO I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- WELL,
I GUESS YOU WOULD KNOW.
- BEING BEATEN UP BY A GIRL
CAN BE PRETTY EMBARRASSING.
- AS YOUR TRAINING PROGRESSES,
YOU'LL BE LESS EMBARRASSING.
- IS THAT YOUR WAY
OF ENCOURAGING ME?
- I'M JUST TELLING YOU
THE WAY THINGS STAND.
- WHICH MEANS I LOOK
REALLY LAME RIGHT NOW.
- HMM.
- Girl: WHAT IS HE DOING?
- ( laughs ) HUH?
- Shana: IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW YOU LOOK.
YUJI, WHAT'S IMPORTANT
IS THAT YOU GET STRONGER,
SO THAT WE CAN FIGHT TOGETHER.
YOU HAVE TO GET MUCH STRONGER.
OH, HERE,
I'VE GOT ONE YEN.
- ( bells tolling )
- YOU BUYIN' LUNCH TODAY?
- MM-HMM.
- SO HOW'S BIG SISTER?
- ABOUT THE SAME.
- TOO BAD.
I GUESS WHEN SHE'S FEELING
A BIT BETTER,
SHE'S GONNA TAKE OFF
AND LEAVE THE CITY.
- MAYBE.
- DON'T GET ME WRONG!
I REALLY WANT BIG SISTER
TO GET BETTER, HONESTLY!
I SWEAR IT!
- YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW.
- OH, MAN, I'M STARVING.
- MMM.
- OGATA!
- ( gasps )
- YOU WANNA COME EAT WITH US?
- UH, SURE.
- MMM!
DID YOU MAKE THESE, KAZUMI?
THEY LOOK GREAT!
- I AM AMAZED!
- I GOT THE RECIPE
FROM MY FRIEND,
SO I THOUGHT
I'D GIVE IT A TRY.
- Ogata:
WHY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
PLEASE,
OR DON'T YOU LIKE THESE?
- SURE, I'LL HAVE ONE.
THANK YOU.
- WOULD YOU LIKE ONE?
- SURE, THANK YOU.
- Ogata: DELICIOUS!
- WOW, THIS IS WAY BETTER
THAN STORE-BOUGHT.
- YEP, TASTY!
- OH, YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- YOU KNOW, YOSHIDA,
YOU'RE A GOOD COOK.
- OH, NO,
I JUST REALLY LOVE BAKING.
- IT'S GOOD,
BUT I'M NOT ENJOYING IT.
- EXCUSE ME, ARE THERE
ANY LIBRARY COMMITTEE MEMBERS?
- OVER HERE!
THAT'S THE TWO OF US.
- DO YOU HAVE A MOMENT?
THEY'VE CHANGED THE SCHEDULE
AND THEY'RE GOING TO BE
RESTACKING THE BOOKS TODAY.
REPORT TO THE LIBRARY
AFTER SCHOOL.
- WHAT, YOU MEAN TODAY?
- EVERY CLASS
HAS TO SEND TWO PEOPLE,
SO IF YOU CAN'T MAKE IT, TRY TO
FIND SOMEONE TO GO FOR YOU.
- YOU CAN'T GO?
- NO, MY FAMILY AND I
ARE VISITING MY GRANDMA
IN THE HOSPITAL.  SHE'S SICK.
- REALLY.
- HUH?  WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE HER PLACE, SAKAI,
AND YOU GO WITH YOSHIDA?
- I HAVE PREP SCHOOL TODAY,
BUT YOU'RE
NOT DOING ANYTHING, RIGHT?
- I'M FREE.
- WELL, THAT'S IT THEN!
ARE YOU FINE WITH THAT, YOSHIDA?
- BUT I'D BE IMPOSING.
- WE HAVE TO SEND TWO
PEOPLE ANYWAY. I'LL DO IT.
- Ogata: OH, THANK YOU.
I OWE YOU ONE!
- NO, HE CAN'T MAKE IT.
- All: HUH?
- BUT WHY NOT?
- MMM.
- HUH?  OH.
- TODAY AFTER SCHOOL
I'M GONNA SET UP A SEAL
SO WE CAN PRACTICE
SOME BIGGER MOVES.
- WHAT?
DO YOU HAVE PREVIOUS PLANS?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT,
I JUST REMEMBERED
THAT I ASKED HIRAI
TO SHOW ME HER NOTES LATER.
SORRY, BUT WE'LL HAVE TO DO IT
SOME OTHER TIME.
- SHE SEEMS UPSET.
- I WAS THE ONE WHO ASKED HER.
I'LL GO APOLOGIZE PROPERLY.
SHANA, I'M SORRY,
BUT IT HAS TO DO
WITH THE SCHOOL COMMITTEE.
WE CAN DO OUR TRAINING
LATER ON THIS EVENING.
- I THINK I MADE IT CLEAR WE
WERE GONNA DO IT AFTER SCHOOL.
- I DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE.
- YOU COULD HAVE REFUSED.
- LOOK, I ALREADY SAID I'D GO.
IT'S TOO LATE NOW.
- GETTING YOU TRAINED
IS MORE IMPORTANT.
- SURE, BUT...
SCHOOL'S IMPORTANT TOO.
- THIS IS MORE IMPORTANT!
AND WE AGREED FIRST.
- HEY,
I ALREADY SAID I'M SORRY.
- YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO ASKED TO BE TRAINED, YUJI.
- I KNOW,
BUT IT'S JUST ONE DAY!
- AH!  YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS
ENOUGH ABOUT THIS.
- NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO TODAY.
- AND WHY NOT?
- I JUST DON'T!
- YEAH, WELL, THAT'S NOT A
GOOD ENOUGH REASON!
I'M HELPING OUT
THE COMMITTEE TODAY.
- LISTEN, YUJI,
YOU REALLY HAVE TO TRAIN MORE.
HONESTLY, YOU'RE JUST TOO WEAK,
AND YOU'RE SO DAMNED CLUMSY.
YOU'RE WORSE THAN USELESS,
YOU CAN'T EVEN HELP
ME RIGHT NOW.
- HMM?
- AND THAT'S WHY--
- YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
- YUJI.
- Ogata: HOW WAS HIRAI?
- YEAH, EVERYTHING'S FINE.
SHE WASN'T THAT UPSET.
WE TALKED AND SHE JUST GOT
A FEW THINGS OFF OF HER MIND.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- GUESS YOU'LL BE STAYING LATE
WITH SAKAI, YOSHIDA.
- YEAH.
- ( bird tweeting )
- Chigusa: AH, SHANA-CHAN,
ARE YOU ALONE? WHERE'S YUJI?
- HUH?  OH, HE'S GOT SOME KIND
OF COMMITTEE MEETING.
- OH.
DO YOU WANNA WAIT INSIDE?
I MADE SOME DELICIOUS PUDDING.
- HMM?
- SO YOU LIVE ALONE, DON'T YOU?
THAT MUST BE HARD.
- NO, I'M USED TO IT.
MMM, THIS IS REALLY GOOD.
CHIGUSA'S IS MUCH BETTER.
- GOOD.
GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
YOU KNOW, SHANA-CHAN,
YOU SHOULD STAY
FOR DINNER TONIGHT.
- HUH?
- DAMN.
- WHAT'LL I DO?
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO WALK HOME TOGETHER.
WE'LL HAVE TO TALK.
WHAT IF I RUN OUT OF THINGS
TO SAY?
AH!
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- UH-HUH.
- Girl:
HEY, I JUST HEARD ABOUT THIS.
YOU KNOW HIRAI FROM CLASS TWO?
SHE'S BEEN GETTING HUNDREDS
ON ALL OF HER TESTS.
- I KNOW!  AND SHE'S TOP
OF THE CLASS IN PHYS ED TOO.
GUESS PEOPLE LIKE HER
DO EXIST.
- UM, I, UH...
- YES?
- WELL, I-- NOTHING.
I HAVE TO ASK HIM
ABOUT YUKARI.
IF I KEEP THINKING ABOUT IT
LIKE THIS, I'M GONNA GO CRAZY.
I REALLY HAVE TO KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF YUKARI?
- WHAT?
- MMM.
THOSE GIRLS FROM CLASS THREE
WERE TALKING ABOUT HER.
SHE'S COOL, ISN'T SHE?
- UM, YEAH.
SHE'S SOMETHING, ALL RIGHT.
SHE SURE IS.
IT'S A LITTLE OVERWHELMING.
- IDIOT.  IDIOT!
SHOW A LITTLE BACKBONE.
- Yuji: I'M HOME!
HUH?
- THAT WAS A LONG DAY FOR YOU.
WE ALREADY HAD SUPPER,
AND SHANA-CHAN
EVEN HAD TIME TO TAKE A BATH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS DRESS WAS MINE,
BUT I CONVINCED HER
TO TRY IT ON FOR SIZE.
- UH, YEAH,
LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
- IT'S GETTING LATE. YOU SHOULD
WALK HER HOME NOW, YU-CHAN.
- MOM SURE WOULD BE SHOCKED
IF SHE FOUND OUT
YOU WERE ACTUALLY STAYING IN MY
ROOM AT NIGHT, WOULDN'T SHE?
SHANA?
- WE'LL BEGIN TODAY'S TRAINING.
- NO WAY.
FORGET IT.  IT'S TOO LATE.
- HUH?  YUJI.
- SEE YA.
- WHY?
- Alastor: IT SEEMS
WHEN YOU GET RIGHT DOWN TO IT,
HE DOESN'T QUITE
HAVE WHAT IT TAKES.
- IF ONLY A DENIZEN
WOULD SHOW UP.
EVEN ANOTHER FLAME HAZE.
IF WE HAD TO FIGHT,
THEN I'M SURE YUJI WOULD FOCUS.
HUH?  A SEAL.
BUT WHAT?
- POWER OF EXISTENCE!
MY SWEET POWER OF EXISTENCE!
AAH!
- Marco: WHAT'S THIS?
IS THAT A RINNE?
- FEELS LIKE IT.
- Marco: WHAT A PATHETIC EXCUSE
FOR A SEAL.
ARE YOU GONNA GO?
- I WAS THINKING ABOUT IT,
BUT I CAN'T REMEMBER ANY RHYMES.
- Marco: WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU'RE THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES!
- IT'S THE TRUTH
AND THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
I CAN'T REMEMBER A SINGLE VERSE.
I'M IN ROUGH SHAPE.
HUH?
THERE YOU GO.
WE'LL LET THE LITTLE BRAT
HANDLE IT.
- YUJI'S NOT COMING.
YUJI'S NOT COMING.
WHY NOT?
I JUST WANTED HIM TO BE--
WHAT'S THAT THING DOING?
- IT'S MINE, IT'S MINE!
- Alastor: IT'S OBVIOUSLY MAD.
IT'S LIKELY A RINNE
THAT HAS LOST ITS MASTER.
- IT HAS NO MASTER?
THEN THAT MEANS IT'S GONNA
DISAPPEAR IN A FEW DAYS.
- Alastor: HMM. NO MATTER
HOW MUCH EXISTENCE
A RINNE CONSUMES,
IT CANNOT USE
THE POWER ITSELF.
- SHUT UP, FLAME HAZE!
TOOL FOR DESTRUCTION,
YOU KILLED MY MASTER,
BUT I'M STILL HERE.
I WILL NOT DISAPPEAR!
- YOU'RE WRONG.
YOUR TIME'S ALMOST UP.
- OH, NO,
I AM GOING TO EXIST.
- AAH!
IT'S MINE, IT'S MINE!
- WHAT THE--
HE'S ALL FLAB.
HIS BODY'S SO SPONGY
IT'S HARD TO CUT.
- ( grunting )
STOP IT, YOU'RE CUTTING
AWAY MY EXISTENCE!
DON'T GO, DON'T GO!
- Chigusa: DO YOU HAVE PLANS
FOR TODAY?
- HMM?
- YOU'VE BEEN ACTING RESTLESS
ALL MORNING.
YOU KEEP LOOKING
OUT THE WINDOW.
- UH, I'M MEETING A FRIEND,
BUT IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
IF I DON'T GO.
- OH?
- IF I SHOW UP,
I WON'T BE ANY HELP ANYWAY.
- DID YOUR FRIEND SAY THAT?
OR IS THAT
WHAT YOU TOLD YOURSELF?
- OW, OW!
- EXISTENCE!
MUST GET POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- GIVE IT UP! YOU'RE GONNA
VANISH NO MATTER
HOW MUCH YOU EAT.
- NO, I WON'T! I REFUSE TO GO.
- DERANGED.
- Alastor: ALTHOUGH IT
HAS A LARGE BODY,
ITS CORE MUST BE QUITE TINY.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO KEEP CUTTING
UNTIL WE DESTROY
THAT CENTER.
- MY EXISTENCE!
MUST EAT MORE POWER
OF EXISTENCE!
- I TOLD YOU IT'S POINTLESS!
- SHUT UP!
AAH!
- DON'T ERASE ME!
DON'T CUT AWAY MY--
- SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
SHUT UP!  SHUT UP!
- Yuji: EXCUSE ME.
- YOU KNOW, YU-CHAN,
ABOUT YOUR FRIEND,
PERHAPS THEY WANT YOU TO COME
BECAUSE THEY THINK YOU CAN HELP.
I THINK THERE ARE TIMES
WHEN YOU CAN HELP A FRIEND OUT
JUST BY BEING THERE FOR THEM.
- THANKS, MOM.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
I THINK THERE ARE TIMES
WHEN YOU CAN HELP A FRIEND OUT
JUST BY BEING THERE FOR THEM.
- SHANA CAN FIGHT
EVEN IF I'M NOT AROUND.
BECAUSE SHE'S SO STRONG.
SHANA?  SHAN--
- I DON'T WANT TO DISAPPEAR.
WHY?
- IT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE A RINNE.
- NO, DON'T DO IT!
I DON'T WANNA BE DESTROYED.
NO, STOP IT.
NO, DON'T DO IT.
DON'T DO IT!
- ( grunting )
- AAH!
I DID EXIST!
- SHANA.
SHANA, ARE YOU OKAY?
- I'M ALL RIGHT,
I'M NOT HURT.
I'M USED TO
THIS SORT OF THING.
I'M JUST A LITTLE TIRED.
- SHANA, I-- I'M SORRY.
- YUJI, WHY?
IT HURTS, YUJI.
IT HURTS TO BE ALONE.
SHANA.
- ( sobbing )
- I'M SORRY.
I LEFT YOU ALONE.
SORRY.
- YOU HAVE TO BECOME STRONGER.
A LOT STRONGER.
- HMM.
I WILL.  I'LL DO IT.
SO THAT WAY
WE CAN STAY TOGETHER.
- AAH!
- YOU BETTER NOT GET
ANY OF THAT GARBAGE ON ME, MAN.
- WOW!
AWESOME, THIS KID'S WALLET
IS PACKED!
I BET HE'S
SOME RICH GUY'S SON.
- HEY, GUESS YOU'D LIKE TO CALL
FOR HELP, WOULDN'T YA?
- NEXT BATTER, HITTING FOURTH,
THE FIRST BASEMAN.
- Tiriel:
THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU ROACHES.
- HUH?  NO WAY!
GET A LOAD OF THIS!
WE GOT OURSELVES
A PRINCESS HERE.
- DEAR BROTHER,
YOU SHOULD HAVE LISTENED.
YOU SHOULD HAVE WAITED
LIKE I TOLD YOU TO.
- AH.
I HAVE BEEN WAITING.
LOOK, I HAVEN'T EATEN
THESE GUYS YET.
- INDEED, YOU HAVEN'T,
BROTHER.
- HEY, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT, HUH?
- I THINK IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW,
DEAR BROTHER.
YOU CAN HELP YOURSELF TO THEM
WHENEVER YOU LIKE.
- All: WHA-- HUH--
- OH, THAT WAS VERY WELL DONE.
YOU REMEMBERED TO LEAVE
JUST ENOUGH OF THEM
TO FORM THREE LITTLE TORCHES.
- OF COURSE,
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT YOU TOLD
ME TO DO, SISTER TIRIEL.
- ( laughs )
I'M PLEASED, DEAR BROTHER.
- ( choir chanting )
- THOSE TWO,
SORATH AND TIRIEL,
"ENGULFED IN SELF-LOVE,"
"ENGULFED IN LOVE FOR OTHERS."
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: A FLAME HAZE IS
GROWING UP AS A NORMAL GIRL.
ALASTOR AND CHIGUSA DECIDE
TO HAVE A TALK ABOUT HER.
WHAT IS THIS SPECIAL OATH
THAT SHANA LEARNS ABOUT?
NEXT EPISODE...