- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED
IN SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL
WHEN THE WORLD IS DISPLACED
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA MAKE ME
THANK YOU, ARE YOU?
- DON'T BOTHER.
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING
TO BRING THAT STUPID FIGHT
TO AN END.
OH MY, DID I UPSET YOU?
- SOMEDAY YOU AND I ARE GONNA
SETTLE THIS, ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- Yuji: SHE WAS THE FIRST FLAME
I'D SEEN, OTHER THAN SHANA.
THEY'RE SO DIFFERENT.
- HMM, YOU'VE CHANGED
SINCE WE LAST MET.
YOU'RE STILL FULL OF ENERGY,
EVEN THOUGH YOU JUST FOUGHT
A TOUGH BATTLE.
- Marco: OOH, GREAT!
WE LOVE A GOOD FIGHT.  HOO!
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
OUR TOP PRIORITY HAS SET OFF
ONE OF OUR TRIP-WIRES.
- ( Marco laughing )
I KNEW HE'D MAKE HIS MOVE
WITH ALL THIS COMMOTION.
- I'LL PLAY WITH YOU
SOME OTHER TIME, LITTLE GIRL.
- Alastor: WAIT, IF YOU'RE GOING
AFTER THE CORPSE COLLECTOR,
HE HASN'T DONE ANY HARM.
- THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS AN INNOCENT DENIZEN.
- Marco: WE'RE JUST GONNA
GO BLAST HIM AND SMASH HIM.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
- HMM.
- Alastor: LET THEM GO.
YOU DON'T WANT TO FACE THEM SO
SOON AFTER YOU'VE JUST FOUGHT.
LET THEM CHASE AFTER HIM.
THE CORPSE COLLECTOR
WON'T BE CAUGHT THAT EASILY.
- Yuji: IT'S PRETTY SURPRISING.
YOU'RE BOTH FLAME HAZES, BUT YOU
TWO COULDN'T BE MORE DIFFERENT.
SHE'S KINDA LIKE A KNIFE
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- WELL, COMPARED TO HER,
A KNIFE IS PRETTY CUTE.
- Alastor: THERE'S NO DOUBT,
SHE'S A UNIQUE CASE.
HER HATRED FOR DENIZENS
FAR OUTWEIGHS
HER DUTY TO KEEP THE BALANCE.
- HATRED?
- Alastor: BASICALLY, HUMANS
BECOME FLAME HAZES
AS A RESULT OF INJURIES
OR TRAGEDIES SUFFERED
AT THE HANDS OF A DENIZEN.
HATRED AND A DESIRE FOR REVENGE
ARE HER SOLE REASONS
FOR FIGHTING.
- WHAT ABOUT SHANA?
- Alastor: SHE IS ALSO UNIQUE,
BUT IN A DIFFERENT WAY.
SHE'S LIKELY
THE ONLY FLAME HAZE
WHO DOESN'T HARBOR SOME KIND
OF GRUDGE AGAINST DENIZENS.
- I SEE.
- WHAT?
- LISTEN, COULD YOU TEACH ME
HOW TO FIGHT?
- TEACH YOU?
- WE WERE ABLE TO PUT A STOP
TO THE CITY DEVOURING,
BUT WHAT DO WE DO IF MORE
CRIMSON DENIZENS
SHOW UP ALL OF A SUDDEN?
SO I THOUGHT
WITH A LITTLE HARD WORK,
I COULD TRAIN
AND HELP YOU OUT.
- YOU WANNA FIGHT TOGETHER?
- WHY NOT?
- HUH.  I GUESS
WE COULD GIVE IT A TRY.
- YOU UPSET?
- I'M NOT UPSET, YUJI.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
WHY ARE YOU RUNNING OFF?
- I FEEL LIKE I CAN DO ANYTHING,
AS LONG AS I'M WITH YUJI.
- I'M HERE, BUT ARE YOU SURE
THIS IS WHERE IT HAPPENED?
- Tanaka: THAT'S THE PLACE,
I'M POSITIVE.
- Margery: WELL, I'M LOOKING,
BUT THERE'S NO SIGN
OF HIM HERE NOW.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
- ANY SIGN OF HIS FLAME?
- NOT ANYMORE, THERE ISN'T.
- ( sighs )
- Marco: HE'S A SLIPPERY ONE.
HE PROBABLY REALIZED HE WALKED
INTO AN UNRESTRICTED METHOD
AND THEN FLED
INTO A CROWD SOMEWHERE.
- Margery:
EVEN SO, I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW FAST HE'S MOVING
AROUND DOWN THERE.
USUALLY I CAN PICK UP MOTION
WAVES FROM THAT KIND OF POWER.
- Marco: WELL, IT'S A GOOD
THING WE WERE ABLE
TO SEAL THIS WHOLE CITY
WHILE THE BLAZING-EYED MISSY
WAS KICKING UP A FUSS.
BUT I'M SURE
WE'LL EVENTUALLY RUN INTO HIM.
- GET WITH IT, WILL YOU?
THIS SEAL ISN'T GONNA
LAST FOREVER, YOU KNOW.
KEEP TALKING LIKE THAT
AND HE'S GONNA GET AWAY AGAIN.
- Marco: IF THAT HAPPENS,
THEN WE MAY EVEN SEE
A FEW TEARS FROM THE CHANTER
OF ELEGIES.  HA!  OW!
- I THOUGHT I WAS SO CLEVER
LURING THEM HERE,
BUT NOW IT SEEMS AS IF
I'VE ONLY TRAPPED MYSELF.
THIS WILL BE A TEST
OF PATIENCE.
- ( boys shouting )
- DAMN THAT CORPSE-COLLECTOR
SON A BITCH!
RUNNIN' AND ACTIN'
LIKE A COCKROACH.  AH!
WHAT TRICK IS THAT BASTARD
USING TO MOVE?
EITA, KEISAKU,
YOU'RE FLAME HAZES NOW,
SO YOU GOTTA LEARN
TO KEEP A CLOSER EYE ON HIM.
- SORRY. I'LL BE MORE CAREFUL.
- ( Margery squealing )
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE NOT FLAME HAZES.
- I WANNA HELP BIG SISTER OUT,
SO I'M PRETENDING TO BE ONE.
- REALLY?
- Marco: STOP IT!  HEY!
LET ME DOWN!
- YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN, DUDE.
- SORRY.
- Marco:
WHAT?  COME ON!
- I SAY WHAT'S THE POINT
IN DRINKING
UNLESS YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME
AND JUST GO NUTS?
TOMORROW WE'LL WRITE
TOMORROW'S POETRY.
IF THAT CAN BE DONE,
THEN THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
( laughing )
- SHE'S DOWN.
ARE YOU OKAY, BIG SISTER?
- Marco: SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
THIS HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
- I THOUGHT SHE COULD
HOLD HER LIQUOR.
- Marco: SHE'S ACTUALLY
NOT THAT MUCH OF A DRINKER.
SOMETIMES SHE JUST FEELS
THE NEED.
- YOU TOLD US THAT FLAME HAZES
WERE AVENGERS.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO HER?
TO HER FAMILY
OR MAYBE TO A LOVER?
- Marco: HO-HO-HO,
WANNA SEE FOR YOURSELF?
- HUH?
- Both: UGH!
- Marco: HEH HEH HEH,
SURPRISED?
OW!
- STUPID MARCO.
WHO TOLD YOU
TO SHOW THEM THAT?
- MARGERY DAW,
MY LADY OF ANGER.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH SHOWING THEM?
DON'T YOU SAY
THAT ONLY ALCOHOL
GIVES YOU THE COURAGE
TO TALK ABOUT SOME THINGS?
- MMM.
- ALL THAT BOOZE ON YOUR BREATH
HAS MADE ME EMOTIONAL.
BESIDES, IT'S BEEN A WHILE SINCE
WE'VE HAD SOMEONE TO TALK TO.
- THAT SILVER GUY WE SAW
WAS A CRIMSON DENIZEN?
- I GET IT. HE TOOK THE LIFE
OF SOMEONE CLOSE TO HER.
- NO, NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
- DID YOU GET REVENGE?
- Marco: NOT YET.
DENIZENS HAVE THE ABILITY
TO CHANGE THEIR APPEARANCE.
I'M NOT COUNTING ON HIM
STILL LOOKING LIKE THAT.
BESIDES, WHOEVER HEARD OF A
DENIZEN WITH A SILVER FLAME?
- Both: MMM.
- THAT DOESN'T MEAN WE'RE
GONNA GIVE UP.
THE TWO OF US ARE GONNA KEEP
SEARCHING UNTIL WE FIND HIM.
- HMM.
STUPID MARCO.
I KNEW YOU WERE NOTHING
BUT A BIG SOFTIE.
- Marco: YOU THINK SO?
MAYBE ALL YOUR BOOZING
HAS MADE ME DRUNK TOO.
- WELL, ALL YOUR TALKING
ABOUT THAT NONSENSE
HAS COMPLETELY SOBERED ME UP.
- ( gasps )
- DO YOU FALL IN LOVE
WITH A GIRL'S WEAK SIDE?
- I DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
- ( Marco laughing )
THAT'S IT FOR TONIGHT.
LET'S GET SOME SLEEP.
( laughing )
- BIG SISTER, GOOD NIGHT.
- Marco: SLEEP WELL
AND REST EASY, YOU TWO.
- HYAH!
- UH, AH!
OW, MAN!
OW!  EE!  OW!
COME ON, WAIT A MINUTE!
- I TOLD YOU,
DON'T CLOSE YOUR EYES.
- SURE, BUT I DON'T GET IT.
YOU WANT ME TO KEEP MY EYES OPEN
AND STARE AT A STICK?
DON'T YOU HAVE SOME KIND OF
FIGHTING STYLE OR A TECHNIQUE?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- Alastor: IT APPEARS
HE CAN'T FOLLOW DIRECTIONS
UNLESS HE KNOWS THE REASONING
BEHIND THEM FIRST,
ALTHOUGH REAL TRAINING
INVOLVES SHUTTING UP
AND DOING AS YOU'RE TOLD.
- YOU'RE NOT TEACHING A DOG.
I NEED SOME KIND
OF EXPLANATION HERE.
- HMM.
WHEN YOU'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF A FIGHT,
YOUR MOST IMPORTANT SKILL
IS THE ABILITY TO FEEL THE KILL.
IF YOU'RE ABLE TO DO THAT,
YOU CAN AVOID
YOUR OPPONENT'S LETHAL STRIKE
WHILE FINDING A GAP
FOR YOUR OWN BLOW.
SO FOR OUR FIRST LESSON, I WANT
YOU TO STOP THINKING SO MUCH.
SENSE THE KILL
THAT I'M CREATING WITHIN ME.
- THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY THAT
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
HOW DO I SENSE THIS KILL?
IT IS NOT SOMETHING
THAT YOU CAN THINK ABOUT.
YOU HAVE TO WATCH CAREFULLY
UNTIL YOU CAN SENSE IT.
I REALLY MEAN IT WHEN I SAY
DON'T CLOSE YOUR EYES.
- YOU'RE KIDDING.
- OKAY, GET UP.
- UH, JUST A MINUTE.
AH!
- Alastor: THIS DOESN'T
LOOK PROMISING.
WE COULD BE WASTING
OUR TIME.
- YOU CAN'T EXPECT PERFECTION
ON THE FIRST DAY.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO AGAIN.
- ( chuckles )
- UH, WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S-- IT'S NOTHING.
READY?
- I THINK YOU TWO
HAD BETTER FINISH UP SOON
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO BE LATE
FOR SCHOOL.
SOME TEA, SHANA-CHAN?
- THANK YOU.
- SO THEN,
DOES HE HAVE POTENTIAL?
- NO, HE'S AWFUL.
- HUH?
- OH, I'M SO SORRY
TO HEAR THAT.
- THAT'S BRUTAL,
BUT I GUESS I'M LUCKY
TO HAVE A MOTHER
WHO'S SO UNDERSTANDING.
- YOU'RE GOING TO GIVE HIM
MARTIAL ARTS LESSONS?
THAT'S WONDERFUL!
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
GO EASY ON HIM.
- UH...
- I WON'T.
- WHAT?
- ( sighs )
- OH, SHANA-CHAN,
I DREW A BATH FOR YOU.
WHY DON'T YOU GO IN
AND FRESHEN UP?
YOU DON'T WANNA GO TO SCHOOL
ALL SWEATY, DO YOU?
- WELL...
- NOW QUICK, HOP RIGHT IN
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO BE LATE
THIS MORNING.
- MMM.
- ( Margery moaning )
I'M DYING.
GO AHEAD, FINISH ME OFF.
( grunting )
OH, MY HEAD IS SPINNING.
- ( Marco laughing )
OH, ALCOHOL,
A DOUBLE-EDGED SWORD!
EITHER WAY, I'M NOT GONNA
USE THE CLEANSING FLAME
ON YOU JUST YET.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN FOR NOW,
MARGERY DAW,
MY ANGEL OF DRUNKENNESS!
- STUPID MARCO,
YOU'RE DEAD.
- PLEASE, MR. MARCO,
I'M BEGGING YOU.
DO SOMETHING
TO MAKE HER FEEL BETTER.
- Marco: NOT A CHANCE.
- HMM?
- SPOIL HER NOW AND IT'LL BE
THE SAME THING AGAIN TONIGHT.
( laughing )
- I GUESS WE DON'T WANT THAT.
- I'M FINE WITH HER DRINKING.
- LET'S NOT BE HASTY.
- STUPID MARCO, WHAT IF THE
CORPSE COLLECTOR ESCAPES
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO CRUEL
TO HELP ME?
OW.
- Marco: I'LL CLEANSE YOU
IF HE DECIDES
TO MAKE AN APPEARANCE.
- MMM, LISTEN, YOU TWO.
CHECK THE BUILDING WHERE
THAT FIGHT HAPPENED YESTERDAY.
FOR SOME REASON,
THAT PERVERTED PUPPETEER KNEW
EXACTLY WHERE LAMIES WOULD SHOW.
OH, MY HEAD.
- OOH!
- HE MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING
IN THERE.
- DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE ON IT!
- GUESS WE'RE SKIPPIN' SCHOOL
AGAIN.
- MMM.
- ( door closes )
- ( Marco laughing ) THEY'RE
GOOD KIDS, DON'T YA THINK?
( laughing )
- AW, SHUT UP!  AH!
- ( sighs )
I'VE NEVER CLEANED MY BODY
THIS WAY BEFORE.
- Alastor: CONSIDERING
SHE'S YOUR MOTHER,
SHE'S QUITE LEVEL-HEADED.
- YEAH, NOTHING BOTHERS HER.
- Alastor: INDEED.
- TELL ME, THAT FLAME HAZE
FROM YESTERDAY
IS STILL IN MISAKI, ISN'T SHE?
- MMM.
- WHICH MEANS THAT LAMIES
IS STILL SAFE AND SOUND.
- Alastor: YES, BUT
THOSE TWO SOCIOPATHS
DON'T KNOW
WHEN TO GIVE UP.
THEY'VE COVERED
THE ENTIRE CITY
WITH A SPECIALIZED
UNRESTRICTED METHOD.
- YOU SEEM TO KNOW LAMIES
PRETTY WELL.
- Alastor: FROM LONG AGO.
- HUH.
- BUT MY DESIRE TO PROTECT HIM
IS OF A MORE PRACTICAL NATURE.
IT HAS TO DO WITH THE QUANTITY
OF EXISTENCES
THAT HE HAS COLLECTED.
HE'S BEEN ENGAGED IN THIS
PRACTICE FOR HUNDREDS OF YEARS,
SO IT'S A SIGNIFICANT AMOUNT.
HE'S CAPPED ALL THIS POWER
BY USING AN UNRESTRICTED METHOD
OF HIS OWN CREATION.
- Yuji: I THINK HE TOLD ME
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT.
- Alastor: SHOULD HE BE
ELIMINATED FOR SOME REASON,
A TREMENDOUS
NUMBER OF EXISTENCES
WOULD SUDDENLY BE FREED.
JUST THINK ABOUT THE EFFECT
THAT WOULD HAVE ON THIS WORLD.
- Yuji: I GUESS IT WOULD BE
LIKE A BOMB GOING OFF.
- Alastor: ANYWAY, WE MUST
EITHER MAKE THE CLAWS
AND FANGS OF VIOLATION
AND THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
PROMISE TO LEAVE HIM ALONE,
OR WE MUST GIVE THEM
SUCH A THRASHING
THAT THEY ARE INCAPABLE
OF PURSUING HIM.
EITHER WAY, WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO FIGHT THEM AGAIN.
I ASSUME YOU STILL
HAVE THE AZURE
THAT YOU TOOK FROM THE HUNTER.
- HMM.
IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE GOING TO BE HELPING US
IN THE UPCOMING BATTLES.
I'M STILL NOT CONVINCED
IT'S A GOOD IDEA,
BUT SHANA
HAS HER HEART SET ON IT.
WHAT?
- WELL, ALASTOR,
I THINK THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
YOU'VE EVER CALLED HER SHANA.
- Alastor:
THE NAME COMES IN HANDY
WHEN I'M TALKING
TO YOU ABOUT HER.
- YOU KNOW MY PLAN
WAS TO FIGHT TOGETHER WITH HER
RIGHT FROM THE BEGINNING.
ALTHOUGH I WON'T BE
THAT USEFUL AT FIRST.
- Alastor: JUST DON'T
GET IN OUR WAY.
- I WON'T.
IF I TRY HARD ENOUGH,
I'M SURE I CAN HELP YOU
IN A LOT OF WAYS.
- Shana:
HE USED TO IRRITATE ME,
BUT NOW I CAN FEEL
THIS ENERGY INSIDE ME.
HOW STRANGE.
- Tanaka: BIG SISTER!
- HMM?
- BIG SISTER,
WE FOUND SOMETHING UNUSUAL.
THIS IS MISAKI CITY,
ISN'T IT?
- YEAH, IN GREAT DETAIL TOO.
- Margery: NOW I SEE.
HE WAS USING THE CRYSTAL ALTAR.
HOW CLEVER.
WITH THIS, HE WAS ABLE
TO SEE THE TORCHES
THAT LAMIES
WAS CONSUMING.
- Marco: HE WAS WELL KNOWN
FOR COLLECTING TREASURES.
- WELL, HE WON'T BE NEEDING IT
ANYMORE.  KEISAKU, EITA,
I'M GONNA USE ANOTHER
UNRESTRICTED METHOD
FOR DETECTION.
EVEN IF HE'S MOVING,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO SEE HIM
IN THE CRYSTAL ALTAR.
DON'T MISS IT.
- Both: RIGHT.
- YOU KNOW, WE MIGHT EVEN BE
ABLE TO FIND
THAT SILVER GUY
WITH THIS THING.
- YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
- THIS ALTAR
DOESN'T SHOW DENIZENS,
JUST HUMANS AND TORCHES.
- DAMN, IS THAT ALL?
- BUT WE MAY BE ABLE
TO LEARN SOMETHING
IF WE KEEP AN EYE
ON THE TORCHES.
- HMM,
A CURIOUS CAT'S A LOST CAT.
- HMM?
- NOW LET'S PUT AN END TO THIS.
- Marco: RIGHT ON! MARGERY DAW,
MY SWORD OF VENGEANCE!
- UGH, I HURT ALL OVER.
- YES, YOU NEED TO TOUGHEN UP.
- HEY, I JUST STARTED.
HUH?
- WHAT?
- IT'S YOSHIDA.
I FORGOT.
I GUESS I JUST ABANDONED HER
AND RAN STRAIGHT HOME YESTERDAY.
- MMM.
- I'LL APOLOGIZE.
- HMM?
- LOOK THERE.
- NOW, SHOW YOURSELF,
CORPSE COLLECTOR.
- UGH!
- THAT'S A SPELL OF DETECTION.
- Alastor: WE SHALL
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT.
- LAMIES.
GOT HIM.
HE'S SO CLOSE,
IT WOULD BE EASY TO HEAD THERE
AND WAIT FOR THAT CRAZY WOMAN
TO SHOW UP.
- BUT...
- YUJI!  HURRY UP!
- HMM?
WHAT ARE SAKAI AND YUKARI
DOING TOGETHER?
- KEISAKU, EITA,
I SENSE SOMETHING
IN THE WESTSIDE.  DO YOU SEE IT?
- I'M WATCHING.
YEAH, THERE'S SOMETHING THERE.
- WHOA.  IT'S GONE.
- GONE WHERE?
- CAN'T TELL,
THERE ARE TOO MANY TORCHES.
- UGH!
I'LL DO IT AGAIN.
FIND HIM, AND TRY
NOT TO LOSE HIM THIS TIME.
AAH!
- WHAT'S THAT?
SHE'S USING
THE DETECTION METHOD AGAIN.
HEY, LAMIES IS ON THE MOVE.
HE'S NOWHERE NEAR HERE.
- Alastor:
WHAT INCREDIBLE SPEED.
A SPECIAL UNRESTRICTED METHOD?
- BUT I DIDN'T SENSE ANYTHING
OUT OF THE ORDINARY.
HE'S TRICKY.
HE'LL BE AWFULLY HARD
TO CATCH LIKE THIS.
- UH...
- BIG SISTER,
HE JUST DISAPPEARED AGAIN.
- IS HE CHANGING LOCATIONS
INSTANTLY?
BUT THAT'S A VERY POWERFUL
UNRESTRICTED METHOD.
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO SENSE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- HEY, MARGERY,
CAN OTHER CREATURES
BECOME TORCHES AS WELL?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
ONLY PEOPLE.
THERE SHOULD BE
JUST PEOPLE THERE, RIGHT?
- NO, I CAN SEE
BIRDS HERE, TOO.
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE RIGHT.  HOW COME?
- SEVERAL BIRD TORCHES.
- Marco: YOU KNOW, MAYBE
THE ALTAR IS MALFUNCTIONING.
- HMM.  RIGHT.
I BET THAT'S IT.
KEISAKU, EITA,
WATCH THOSE BIRDS CLOSELY
AND TELL ME WHERE THEY GO.
- Tanaka: GOTCHA!
- HMM.
- Yuji: SHANA,
HAS THAT FLAME HAZE MOVED YET?
- NO, SHE'S USED
HER DETECTION METHOD TWICE,
BUT SHE'S STILL
IN THE SAME PLACE.
- STOP FOR A SECOND.
THINK ABOUT IT, SHANA.
WE'RE BEING FORCED
TO RUN ALL OVER THE CITY HERE.
I BET THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT LAMIES
WANTS THOSE GUYS TO DO.
- HUH?
- IT'S A COMMON STRATEGY
TO USE A FAKE OR A COPY
TO TRICK PEOPLE.
- Alastor: A DECOY MANEUVER.
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
IF LAMIES COULD REALLY
MOVE AROUND THE CITY
AS QUICKLY AS THAT,
THEN HE WOULD HAVE BEEN
LONG GONE BY NOW.
- MMM.
- I THINK WHAT'S
REALLY HAPPENING...
- Alastor: GO ON.
...IS THAT HE ISN'T
ACTUALLY MOVING AT ALL.
- ( gasps )
- Alastor: A SKILLED
UNRESTRICTED-METHOD USER
LIKE LAMIES COULD DO THAT.
- AND IT'S PRETTY STRANGE
THAT EVEN THOUGH
THE OTHER FLAME HAZE
MUST HAVE SPOTTED HIM,
SHE HASN'T BUDGED AN INCH.
MAYBE SHE KNOWS
IT'S SOME KIND OF TRICK.
- DO YOU THINK SHE KNOWS
WHERE HIS REAL LOCATION IS?
- MAYBE.  I BET THEY'LL BE
ON THE MOVE SOON.
THEY'RE JUST WAITING.
- WE'LL ARRIVE TOO LATE
IF WE TRY AND FOLLOW HER.
LAMIES DOESN'T KNOW
HOW TO FIGHT,
SO I'M PRETTY SURE
HE'LL GO DOWN QUICKLY.
WE NEED TO FIND OUT WHERE HE IS
AND THEN GET THERE FIRST.
- I THINK I KNOW.
THE FIRST TIME I SAW HIM
WAS AT THE MUSEUM.
I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT WAS THE REAL LAMIES TOO.
IT'S JUST A FEELING,
BUT I THINK HE'S THERE.
- GRAB ON.
WE'LL HAVE TO FLY.
- HUH?
- COME ON!  THERE'S NO TIME.
- OKAY.  ALL RIGHT.
- YOU HAVE TO HOLD ON
TIGHTER THAN THAT.
- TIGHTER, RIGHT.
- A LOT TIGHTER.
- HOW TIGHT?
- TIGHTER!
- ( grunting )
- WHY IS IT I FEEL STRONGER?
- AH, LAMIES.
HE'S A CLEVER ONE, ALL RIGHT.
HE HAS HIS DUMMY CONSUME A
TORCH, AND WHEN IT'S DETECTED,
HE CHANGES INTO BIRDS
AND COLLECTS THEM
WHILE ACTIVATING ANOTHER DECOY.
THEN HE ABSORBS THE BIRDS
THAT FLY BACK TO HIM,
BECAUSE WE'RE FOLLOWING
THE DUMMIES,
IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S
CHANGING LOCATIONS
ALMOST INSTANTANEOUSLY.
THANK GOODNESS FOR THE ALTAR.
- Marco: GATHERING HIS STRENGTH
A LITTLE BIT HERE,
A LITTLE BIT THERE. HUH, WHAT A
BORING WAY TO DO THINGS.
- KEISAKU, EITA, HAVE ALL THE
BIRDS GATHERED TOGETHER?
- Tanaka: JUST ABOUT.
- I SEE.
THEN I'LL SAY IT NOW
WHILE I HAVE THE CHANCE.
THANK YOU.
- HUH?  WHAT DO YOU MEAN
WHILE YOU HAVE THE CHANCE?
- JUST LIKE I SAID.
WHEN I FINISH THAT GUY OFF,
I'M OUTTA HERE.
- NO WAY, BIG SIS,
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
- BE QUIET.
DENIZENS DON'T APPEAR
THAT OFTEN.
PEOPLE GO THEIR WHOLE LIVES
WITHOUT SEEING ONE.
YOU'VE MET ONE AND SURVIVED,
SO YOU SHOULD BE FINE NOW.
WELL, GOOD-BYE.  I ACTUALLY
ENJOYED MYSELF FOR A CHANGE.
- Marco: HEADS UP
AND STAY SAFE, YOU TWO!
( dying down )
- WHY?
I WANTED TO HELP HER
UNTIL SHE GOT HER REVENGE
ON THOSE WHO'VE WRONGED HER.
- SHE USED US.
AND WHEN SHE WAS FINISHED,
SHE JUST DISAPPEARED.
THANKS A LOT, MARGERY.
- KILL 'EM, KILL 'EM,
KILL 'EM,
KILL 'EM!
KILL THE DENIZENS!
- Alastor: YOU'LL BE FACING
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES AGAIN.
- I WON'T LOSE THIS TIME.
- DO YOU THINK WE'LL MAKE IT
IN TIME?
IF LAMIES DIES,
THIS CITY IS GOING TO--
- DON'T WORRY.
THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
THE DUTY OF A FLAME HAZE
IS TO MAINTAIN THE BALANCE
OF THE WORLD,
NO MATTER WHAT.
- OKAY.
- I FEEL SO POWERFUL!
I CAN DO ANYTHING!
- ( choir chanting )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE FLAME-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER
AND THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
TWO BRIGHT FLAMES.
A CLASH BETWEEN DUTY
AND HATRED.
WHICH WILL SURVIVE?
NEXT EPISODE...