- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- (groans )
( sniggers )
- Margery: I THINK WE'RE IN FOR
A HELLUVA GOOD TIME, MARCOSIAS.
- Marco: YEAH! IT'S BEEN
AGES SINCE WE'VE HAD
A REAL KNOCKDOWN FIGHT,
MARGERY DAW, MY BEAUTIFUL
GOBLET. LET'S GET HIM!
- Alastor: THAT'S SUPREME
THRONE, HECATE.
SHE'S ONE OF THE LEADERS
OF BALL MASQUE.
- WELL, I DON'T CARE WHO SHE IS.
GIVE YUJI BACK TO ME.
- Yuji: SHANA.
- Hecate: YOU BELONG TO ME NOW.
WE'VE ALREADY OPENED OURSELVES
TO EACH OTHER.
( Hecate gasps )
( moans )
- ( gasps )
- Alastor: THIS PRODUCTION
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE,
SHE SEEMS TO BE THE CORE
OF THE ENTIRE SYSTEM.
- I'LL DEFEAT HER
AND STOP IT.
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
- PLAN B!
- Alastor: AS I FEARED,
THE ONLY WAY TO END THIS IS
TO STOP SUPREME THRONE.
WE MUST HURRY! AT THIS RATE,
THE CITY ITSELF MAY COLLAPSE.
- BUT WHAT CAN WE DO
TO STOP IT?
- Yuji: MISAKI CITY.
NO! I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
- ( Hecate exhales )
- Hecate: YOUR THOUGHTS
ARE FULFILLING ME.
IT'S SOMETHING I'VE NEVER BEEN
ABLE TO ACHIEVE BEFORE,
NO MATTER HOW MANY I'VE TOUCHED,
HOW MANY AMBITIONS I'VE FELT.
- Yuji: YOU'RE JUST...
- ( whimpers )
- Bel Peol: IT'S A SHAME.
I THINK WE'RE DONE.
I HAVE TO GO SEE
HOW HECATE IS DOING.
- A LITTLE LONGER.
YOUR PRESENCE IS STILL REQUIRED.
- Tiamat: CONTINUE BATTLE.
- HOW PERSISTENT.
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- Sydonay: HAVING UNLIMITED
ENERGY HAS ITS OWN PROBLEMS.
- Margery: YOU'RE RIGHT.
CONCEIVABLY, WE COULD
FIGHT FOREVER.
- Marco: THOUSAND CHANGES, IS
THIS WHAT YOU GUYS REALLY WANT?
- OR MYSELF, I'D BE
HAPPY JUST TO HAVE
MY HECATE ACHIEVE FULFILLMENT.
- Marco: HUH. ANOTHER WEIRDO.
- Margery: YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE
YOU PLAY WITH DOLLS.
- Tanaka: WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Sato: HEY, LOOK THERE!
- Tanaka: WHAT ARE THOSE?
- Yoshida: IT'S OKAY,
THEY'LL COME BACK. THEY WILL.
SAKAI AND YUKARI.
THEY'VE GOTTA MAKE IT.
- I CAN'T GET ANY CLOSER!
- Alastor: YOU MUST GET
YUJI SAKAI OUT OF THERE.
SEPARATE HER FROM
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD,
AND WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO STOP THIS MADNESS.
- I'M ON IT.
- Yuji: ARE YOU SAYING
YOU'RE SATISFIED
FULFILLING YOURSELF WITH MY
MEMORIES AND MY THOUGHTS?
- Hecate: I'VE ALWAYS DESIRED
IT. I'VE PRAYED FOR IT.
- Yuji: FOR THIS?
- Hecate: YES.
ONCE I MADE CONTACT,
I SUDDENLY REALIZED THAT
THIS IS WHAT I WAS LOOKING FOR.
- Yuji: YOU'RE SHANA! STOP
SAYING YOU'RE ONLY A FLAME HAZE.
AND I'M NOT ONLY A TORCH.
I'M YUJI SAKAI!
- AND NOW I KNOW WHO I AM.
I'VE BEEN SEARCHING FOR MYSELF.
AND NOW I KNOW. I HAVE PROOF.
- I REALLY DO EXIST.
- Yuji: YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHEN WE FIRST MADE CONTACT,
YOU REALLY WERE EMPTY.
- Hecate: BUT NOT NOW.
I AM NO LONGER AN EMPTY VESSEL.
I AM COMPLETELY FULFILLED.
- Yuji: WITH MY MEMORIES.
- Hecate: MY MEMORIES NOW.
- Yuji: YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
- Hecate: HUH?
- Yuji: THERE'S NO POINT
IN FILLING YOURSELF
WITH OTHER PEOPLE'S MEMORIES.
THAT'S NOT YOU.
- Hecate: BUT YOU'RE
JUST A TORCH,
AND YOU'RE FILLED
WITH YUJI SAKAI'S MEMORIES.
- Yuji: YEAH,
AND WHEN I FIRST MET SHANA,
IT'S TRUE THAT I WAS
NOTHING BUT A TORCH,
BUT NOW THINGS ARE DIFFERENT.
- Shana: YUJI.
- Yuji: EVERYTHING IS DIFFERENT.
I KNOW THAT I'M THE ONE
WHO'S DOING ALL THE THINKING,
THE WORRYING, AND THE FEELING.
AND I KNOW FOR A FACT
THAT IT'S ALL TRUE.
- Shana: HA!
- ( grunts )
- Yuji: SO I'M YUJI SAKAI.
WHO ARE YOU?
WHERE ARE YOU? THE REAL YOU?
- ( Hecate sighs )
- Hecate: THE REAL ME.
- ( Shana grunts )
- ( screams )
- Shana: YUJI, I'M HERE!
I'LL SAVE YOU!
- Yuji: SHANA.
- OH, YUJI.
- SHANA!
- ( sobs )
- THE THING THAT WAS
FULFILLING ME IS GONE.
DISAPPEARING.
- Yuji: IT WAS WRONG.
YOU CAN'T FILL YOURSELF
WITH MY MEMORIES.
RIGHT FROM THE VERY BEGINNING,
- YOU'VE BEEN EMPTY.
- Hecate: HUH?
- ( grunts )
- WHAT? IT STOPPED.
- ARE YOU OKAY, SHANA?
- YEAH.
- I'M SORRY.
ALL OF THIS FOR ME.
- DON'T WORRY. THEY
ASKED ME TO BRING YOU BACK.
- HUH?
- THOSE TWO GUYS
AND KAZUMI YOSHIDA.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS? YOU MEAN
EVERYBODY WAS WORRIED ABOUT ME?
- MMM-HMM. BUT I WAS THE
ONE WHO WAS MOST WORRIED.
- SHANA.
- RIGHT FROM THE VERY BEGINNING,
YOU'VE BEEN EMPTY.
- HUH?
- ( screams )
- Sydonay: HECATE!
- HEY, YOU! I THOUGHT WE
AGREED THERE'D BE NO QUITTING!
- ( screaming )
- OH, NO!
- WHAT THE...
- Tiamat: ABNORMAL SITUATION.
- ( screams )
- ALASTOR?
- Alastor: THE SUPREME THRONE
IS SPEWING FORTH
ALL THE POWER OF
EXISTENCE WITHIN HER.
BUT SHE CAN HOLD A TREMENDOUS
AMOUNT OF POWER.
- Yuji: THE CITY!
- ( grunts )
- Yuji: OH, NO.
- Alastor: WITH THIS MUCH
POWER FLOWING FREELY,
WAITING FOR IT TO
DISSIPATE NATURALLY
IS SIMPLY NOT FEASIBLE.
- Yuji: OH, NO.
- ( screams )
- OH, MY GOODNESS!
THIS IS SO EXCITING!
THE REALITY. THE DATA.
THE RESULTS!
FULLY SATURATED
POWER OF EXISTENCE,
EXCEEDING THE WORLD'S
NATURAL SAFETY LIMIT.
- Domino: WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN NOW?
- Professor: GOOD QUESTION.
WE'RE GONNA FIND
OUT PRETTY SOON.
- TIME TO MOVE ON.
- Alastor: THERE'S ONLY
ONE SOLUTION FOR THIS.
- HMM.
- REALLY?
- THE MANIFESTATION OF
ALASTOR, THE FLAME OF HEAVEN.
- Alastor: HMM.
- SO, THEN...
- ALASTOR WILL APPEAR IN
THE WORLD PHYSICALLY.
- Alastor: BEING ONE OF THE MOST
POWERFUL CRIMSON LORDS,
MY MANIFESTATION WILL CONSUME
A GREAT AMOUNT OF EXISTENCE.
IT SEEMS LIKELY MY MANIFESTATION
WILL ABSORB THE EXCESSIVE
AMOUNT OF POWER HERE,
AND AS A RESULT,
PUT A STOP TO THE CITY'S
IMPENDING DESTRUCTION.
- Yuji: THEN...
- Alastor: HOWEVER,
WHEN I MANIFEST,
THE FLAME HAZE WHICH
I OCCUPY IS DESTROYED.
THIS HAS HAPPENED BEFORE.
- BUT BY DESTROYED,
DO YOU MEAN...
- YES, I'LL DIE.
- ( Yuji gasps )
- IT IS THE DESTINY HANDED
TO THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED FLAME HAZE.
IT'S NOT A SURPRISE.
I KNEW THIS WHEN I ENTERED INTO
THE CONTRACT WITH ALASTOR.
- I'M GETTING A BAD
FEELING ABOUT THIS INDEED.
- Tiamat: HURRY.
- Shana: I SAVED YOU, YUJI...
AS SHANA.
NOW I HAVE TO CARRY OUT
MY MISSION AS A FLAME HAZE.
THAT'S WHO I AM.
BUT NOW...
- Alastor: YUJI SAKAI,
UNFORTUNATELY, WE HAVE NO WAY
TO GET YOU TO SAFETY IN TIME.
- LET'S GO.
I DECIDED LONG AGO,
I'D GO WHERE YOU GO.
AND I STILL FEEL THAT WAY.
- YUJI.
- TENPAJYOSAI.
- I LOVE YOU, YUJI SAKAI.
- Wirhelmina: OH, NO!
- Tiamat: TENPAJYOSAI.
- NO! THE ENERGY IS DISSIPATING!
THERE'S ONLY ONE
THING LEFT TO DO!
- Professor: SKY!
- Domino: I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- Professor: WE SHALL MOVE
ON TO OUR NEXT EXPERIMENT!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU WANNA DIE?
- Marco: MOVE IT!
IF WE'RE ENGULFED BY THE FLAME
OF HEAVEN, WE'RE DONE FOR!
- NOTHING. I'M NOTHING.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT,
HECATE. BE CALM.
YOU ARE YOU.
- THAT LITTLE BRAT.
- Shana: WHAT?
- Yuji: SHANA.
- Shana: WHO IS THAT?
- Shana: YUJI? BUT WHY?
- Yuji: WAKE UP.
- Shana: WAKE UP?
BUT I'M NOT...
- Yuji: SHANA! SHANA!
THANK GOODNESS.
- WHY AM I STILL ALIVE?
- Alastor: YOUR BODY WAS ABLE TO
CONTAIN MY PHYSICAL EXISTENCE.
I'D SENSED THIS POSSIBILITY WHEN
WE'D FORGED OUR CONTRACT, BUT...
- Yuji: YOU'RE SAYING WE CAN
DO THIS ALL THE TIME?
- Alastor: DO NOT BE FOOLISH.
WE CAN'T RISK OUR LIVES
ON WHAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
A LUCKY OCCURRENCE.
- NO WAY, I AM ALIVE.
- Yuji: MMMM-HMM.
AND ME, TOO.
- YUJI.
- ( gasps )
- Hmm?
- Yuji: UH, YOU'RE KIND OF...
- ( gasps )
- YOU WERE LOOKING!
- NO.
- YOU WERE LOOKING ALL RIGHT.
- I DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
- THEN WHY'D YOU LOOK AWAY?
- WELL, BECAUSE...
- STOP LOOKING!
- SHANA, YOU MOVED!
- SHUT UP! SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: HUH?
- Wirhelmina: EXCUSE ME FOR
WHAT I'M ABOUT TO DO, INDEED.
- WIRHELMINA.
Margery: THEY'RE PRETTY
LUCKY ALL RIGHT.
- Marco: OH, LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE TAKE OFF FOR A LITTLE WHILE
AND ALL HELL BREAKS LOOSE.
- YOU'VE GOT A POINT.
I GUESS WE COULD
HANG OUT A LITTLE.
- ( Margery laughs )
- Marco: YOU TWO HELP ME!
SHE'S SPINNING ME AROUND!
- ISN'T IT GREAT?
BIG SISTER'S GONNA STICK AROUND!
- I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S A
GOOD THING OR A BAD THING.
- OH, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
BE MORE HONEST
WITH YOUR FEELINGS!
- SEE YOU LATER! BYE!
SHANA-CHAN, I'M SETTING A PLACE
FOR YOU, SO DROP BY FOR SUPPER!
- UH, HI.
- MORNING.
- HEY!
- MORNING!
- THIS SEMESTER,
YOU'VE GOT COMPETITION.
- IKE, WAIT A MINUTE!
- I AM NOT GONNA LOSE TO YOU.
- HUH?
- ROUND NUMBER TWO STARTS TODAY.
- WHAT? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHEN I BROUGHT YUJI BACK,
YOU THANKED ME WITH
TEARS IN YOUR EYES.
- AND THAT WAS
THE END OF ROUND ONE.
MAY THE BEST GIRL WIN. SEE YA!
- WELL, I'M NOT GONNA LOSE.
YOU CAN BET ON IT.
- Yuji: FOR NOW, WE'RE GONNA
LIVE OUR LIVES THE BEST WE CAN,
A SHORT DISTANCE AWAY FROM
WHERE THE WORLD IS DISPLACED.