- Alastor: A HEARTBEAT
THAT LASTS FOR ETERNITY.
LIVES CONSUMED IN
SOUNDLESS BALLS OF FIRE.
NO ONE CAN TELL WHEN
THE WORLD IS DISPLACED,
AND THE FLAMES OF THE
CRIMSON WORLD SWEEP OVER ALL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
YOU'RE THE ONE I CAME TO SEE.
- I MUST DESTROY IT
BEFORE THEY GET IT.
- Yuji: SHANA!
- DID SHE JUST PROTECT
THE MYSTES? HOW RIDICULOUS.
- Yuji: SHANA, SHANA!
- YUJI. I DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO.
- Alastor: STILL NO MOVEMENT
FROM THE PALACE OF STARS.
DO NOT WORRY. SHE SHOULD
BE WAKING UP ANY MOMENT NOW.
AS FAR AS I CAN SEE,
THE GIRL HAS BEEN
STRUGGLING WITH EMOTIONS
WE COULD NOT HAVE
TAUGHT HER ABOUT
AT THE PALACE OF HEAVEN'S ROAD.
IT'S BEEN LIKE THIS EVER SINCE
SHE MET THAT MYSTES.
EMOTIONS THAT SHE
NEVER KNEW SHE HAD,
FEELINGS THAT SHE HAS
NO CONTROL OVER,
- Wirhelmina: HOW COULD
SHE FEEL FOR A MYSTES?
- Alastor:
THAT'S A SILLY QUESTION,
SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING.
WE DID NOT TEACH HER THIS,
BUT BOTH OF US KNOW
WHAT HER MIND IS LIKE.
IT IS CLEAR THE GIRL DOES NOT
TRULY UNDERSTAND
WHAT IS HAPPENING TO HER.
THEREFORE, SHE GETS IRRITATED.
- THAT'S INDEED UNDERSTANDABLE.
THAT BEING SAID, THE MISSION
OF A FLAME HAZE
MUST NOT BE UNDULY
INFLUENCED BY SUCH EMOTIONS.
ESPECIALLY IF THEY'RE
TAKING ON THE MANTLE
OF THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED ONE.
- Alastor: THE GIRL
UNDERSTANDS THAT.
AND THUS, THE CONFUSION.
- Sato: HERE YOU GO.
- YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
- I, I'M SORRY.
- DAMN IT ALL. WHAT DO YOU
THINK THOSE DENIZENS
HAVE PLANNED FOR SAKAI ANYWAY?
- I'M PRETTY SURE THEY WANT
THAT MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
THING INSIDE HIM.
- SO, DOES THAT MEAN THEY'RE
GONNA HAVE TO KILL HIM
TO GET AT THAT DOOHICKEY?
- Yoshida: OH, NO.
- ( sobs )
- DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL SAVE HIM FIRST.
- WHA...
YOU MEAN US TWO?
- WHO ELSE IS GONNA DO IT?
THAT OTHER FLAME HAZE
AND EVEN HIRAI WERE TRYING
TO KILL HIM, REMEMBER?
- ( door closes )
- ( grunts )
- SO, WHAT'S THIS?
- BIG SISTER
LEFT A WEAPON BEHIND.
- ( grunts )
- Tanaka: SHE HELD IT
IN JUST ONE HAND,
BUT WE CAN'T EVEN LIFT
THE THING OFF THE GROUND.
- OH CRAP.
- Yoshida: IT'S JUST
TOO DIFFERENT.
- DIFFERENT? WHAT'S DIFFERENT?
- WE'RE DIFFERENT FROM
YUKARI AND THE OTHERS.
SAKAI'S LIKE THEM.
- ( sighs )
- RIGHT UP TO WHEN
SAKAI WAS TAKEN AWAY,
YUKARI FOUGHT
TO SAVE HIM.
ALL I COULD DO WAS WATCH.
- YOSHIDA.
- Tanaka: IF ONLY
BIG SISTER WAS HERE.
- Sato: TALKING ABOUT
IT WON'T DO ANY GOOD.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES HERE NOW.
- SURE, BUT DO YOU REALLY
THINK WE CAN RESCUE HIM?
I HATE TO SAY IT, BUT MAYBE
WE'RE JUST OVERREACTING 'CAUSE
BIG SISTER ABANDONED
US LIKE THAT.
- Yoshida: ALL OF THIS, THIS IS
YUKARI AND SAKAI'S WORLD.
I CAN GET CLOSER,
BUT I CAN'T BE WITH HIM.
IT'S SO PAINFUL.
I CAN'T STAND THIS.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING TO HELP HIM.
OH, SAKAI.
- ( wind blowing )
- Sydonay: ARE YOU OKAY
WITH THIS, HECATE?
- Hecate: I DO NOT MIND,
IF THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
WILL FULFILL MY DESIRES.
- Sydonay: HMM.
- Bel Peol: ARE YOU STILL
WORRYING FOR NO REASON,
THOUSAND CHANGES?
HECATE IS GONNA HELP US MEET
OUR NEED FOR POWER OF EXISTENCE,
'TIL THE END OF TIME.
- IT WORRIES ME WHEN YOU TALK
ABOUT MEETING OUR NEEDS.
IT MEANS YOU'RE GOING TO
DO SOMETHING TO MY PURE HECATE,
AREN'T YOU?
- Bel Peol: NOTHING WILL CHANGE.
IN FACT, HER PURITY IS
A NECESSARY QUALITY
FOR THE WHOLE SACRED CHAPEL.
WELL, THEN,
THE PREPARATIONS FOR
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
SHOULD BE IN PLACE BY NOW.
- WHERE AM I?
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
- HUH?
- YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE AWAKE.
- YUJI.
- ( moans )
- Alastor: CALM DOWN.
NOTHING HAS CHANGED SINCE THEY
TOOK HIM TO THE PALACE OF STARS.
BALL MASQUE HAS A USE FOR
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE PLANNING EXACTLY
I'M WORRIED OVER WHAT THE JUDGE
OF PARADOXES SAID TO ME.
- BEL PEOL'S WORDS?
- Alastor: HMM, THAT
THIS PLACE WILL BECOME
A FOUNT OF EXISTENCE.
- A FOUNT OF EXISTENCE.
- THE TREASURE'S DEFINING TRAIT
IS THAT IT MAKES POSSIBLE A
COMPLETE RECOVERY
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE.
THEREFORE...
- ARE THEY INDEED GOING
TO USE THE MYSTES
TO CARRY OUT THIS PLAN?
- VERY LIKELY, HOWEVER,
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD IS ONLY
ABLE TO RECOVER WHAT WAS LOST
DURING THE PRECEDING DAY.
GIVEN THE LIMITED SIZE OF
THE MYSTES IN QUESTION,
THAT DOESN'T AMOUNT
TO VERY MUCH AT ALL.
- Wirhelmina: THEN IT
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE TO GO
TO ALL THIS TROUBLE.
- Alastor: HMM, ALL THE
MORE REASON TO THINK
THIS IS ONLY PART OF
A GREATER SCHEME.
- Wirhelmina: INDEED,
MIDNIGHT IS NOT FAR OFF.
- YUJI.
- WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE FORGOTTEN.
- BEGIN, HECATE.
- MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- Bel Peol: HECATE, THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD IS WHAT YOU DESIRE.
IT IS GOING TO FULFILL YOU.
MERELY TOUCH
YOUR BODIES TOGETHER.
- Sydonay: TOUCH BODIES? UGH,
I DON'T LIKE THIS VERY MUCH.
WHY DOES MY HECATE HAVE TO
PHYSICALLY TOUCH THE MYSTES?
- BUT THAT'S THE
VERY ESSENCE OF HER POWER.
NO ONE ELSE CAN DO
WHAT SHE DOES.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- SUPREME THRONE, HECATE.
- HECATE.
- PLEASE OPEN YOUR BODY.
REVEAL YOURSELF.
- I'M EXPENDING.
- ( sighs )
- Yuji: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
IT FEELS GOOD.
- GOOD.
- ( bell tolling )
- I CAN FEEL IT. INFINITE
POWER, FULFILLING ME.
- Bel Peol: THE TREASURE
IS ABOUT TO GET BIG SURPRISE.
AFTER MERGING WITH
THE MYSTES,
HECATE WILL TAKE
IN VAST AMOUNTS.
HER BODY KNOWS NO LIMITS.
- Sydonay: YOU TALK ABOUT HER
LIKE SHE'S SOME KIND OF MONSTER.
SHE'S A PURE EXISTENCE
WHO CAN NEVER BE FULFILLED.
SO SHE WILL NEVER BE TAINTED.
- ANYWAY, THAT IS WHY THE
MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD IS GOING TO
PRODUCE AN UNLIMITED
AMOUNT OF POWER OF EXISTENCE.
IN ADDITION, THE
SEEKER'S CONSTRUCT
WILL CONTINUOUSLY DRAIN
THE POWER AS IT IS
REPLENISHED BY THE TREASURE,
ENSURING THE BODY
WILL ALWAYS BE EMPTY.
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD WILL
BE IN OPERATION PERPETUALLY.
THE POWER OF EXISTENCE
THAT HAS BEEN TAPPED
WILL BEGIN TO FLOW
FROM THE PALACE OF STARS,
AND THE NEEDS OF THE LAND
WILL BE SATISFIED.
- LIKE A FOUNTAIN
THAT FLOWS UNENDINGLY.
- Wirhelmina: No.
- IS THAT POWER OF EXISTENCE?
- THIS IS INDEED A GRAVE MATTER.
- Tiamat: MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- LIKELY PRODUCED BY A DEVICE
CREATED BY THE SEEKER.
- Wirhelmina: THIS WILL
INDEED CAUSE A GREAT AMOUNT
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE
TO GATHER IN THE CITY.
THE BALANCE OF THE ENTIRE
WORLD IS IN JEOPARDY.
- Alastor: I DIDN'T EXPECT
THINGS TO PROGRESS THIS QUICKLY.
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE TIME TO
GATHER OTHER HUNTERS
TO OUR SIDE.
- Wirhelmina: INDEED THE ONLY
ONES WHO CAN STOP THEM
ARE THE FEW OF US
WHO ARE HERE NOW.
- Tiamat: INTO THE ENEMY'S LAIR.
- DEALING WITH
THE MYSTES IS KEY.
DESTROYING IT WOULD INDEED BE
OUR BEST, MOST REALISTIC PLAN
TO DISRUPT THE OPERATION
THEY'VE PUT INTO MOTION HERE.
INDEED AS FLAME HAZES, WE CANNOT
AFFORD FAILURE AT THIS TIME.
BUT BEFORE THAT, WE HAVE
TO HEAL YOUR WOUNDS.
- YUJI.
- THEN WHAT ELSE AM
I SUPPOSED TO DO?
SHANA, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING THROUGH YOUR HEAD.
I KNOW. I'M A MYSTES
AND YOU'RE ONLY A FLAME HAZE.
RIGHT? I BET YOU'RE GOING
TO DESTROY ME, AREN'T YOU?
- I WOULDN'T.
I DEFINITELY WOULDN'T.
BUT I COULDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
- Alastor: WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO WITH YUJI SAKAI?
- I DON'T...
- Alastor: OR RATHER,
WHAT DO YOU WANT HIM TO DO?
- INDEED I BELIEVE YOU.
- Alastor: SHANA.
- IS THAT...
IT'S BLOODSUCKER.
WHAT IS IT DOING HERE?
- BIG SISTER, MARGERY,
LEFT IT BEHIND.
- YOU'RE GONNA GO FIGHT
THOSE DENIZENS, RIGHT?
WE BROUGHT IT
OVER HERE TO GIVE TO YOU.
- PLEASE, USE IT
TO RESCUE SAKAI.
- WE'RE BEGGING YOU.
WE WANTED TO SAVE HIM
OURSELVES, BUT IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- THIS IS THE ONLY THING WE
COULD COME UP WITH TO HELP HIM.
- HIRAI, YOU'VE GOTTA
SAVE HIS LIFE, PLEASE!
- WE'RE NOT ASKING
THE FLAME HAZE TO DO THIS.
WE'RE ASKING
YUKARI HIRAI TO SAVE HIM.
- HMM.
- PLEASE HIRAI.
- I BEG YOU.
- Sato: WE'RE GONNA GO
TO THE CRYSTAL ALTAR.
- HUH?
- YEAH, MAYBE WE'LL BE ABLE
TO HELP YOU OUT FROM THERE.
- Alastor: ASKING
YUKARI HIRAI...
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
HUMAN BEINGS HAVE EVER
MADE THAT REQUEST.
- Yoshida: IT LOOKS LIKE
SATO AND TANAKA AND I
ALL HAD THE SAME THOUGHT.
- I DON'T WANNA HEAR IT.
- TRUTH IS, I DON'T
WANNA SAY IT.
- IF I WAS YOU, YUKARI,
I COULD GO RESCUE HIM.
I CAN'T STAND THIS.
IN A SITUATION LIKE THIS,
YOU AND SAKAI ARE JUST
CLOSER TO EACH OTHER.
- WE'RE CLOSER TO EACH OTHER?
- BUT THAT GIVES ME
FAITH IN YOU.
SO, I BELIEVE IN YOU, YUKARI.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE THE FEELING OF
LOVE IS THE SAME FOR EVERYONE.
I BELIEVE IN YOU, BECAUSE I
THINK YOU REALLY LOVE SAKAI.
- BECAUSE I...
- Wirhelmina: I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR YOU.
- HUH?
- IF YOU DON'T GET SOME REST,
THEN YOUR INJURIES WILL INDEED
TAKE LONGER TO HEAL.
DESTROYING THE MYSTES IS A
MATTER OF THE GRAVEST URGENCY.
LET'S BE OFF.
- Yoshida: YUKARI,
I'LL BE WAITING.
COME BACK WITH SAKAI.
- RIGHT.
- OH, PLEASE. I'M SURE YOU'LL DO
IT, BECAUSE I KNOW YOU LOVE HIM.
- YUJI, I CAN FEEL YOU.
- Bel Peol: THIS ENTIRE
CITY WILL BECOME ONE
SOLID MASS OF EXISTENCE.
HAS THERE EVER BEEN ANYONE
WHO HAS GAINED SUCH POWER?
NAY, I, JUDGE OF PARADOXES, WILL
BECOME THE FIRST TO CONTROL IT.
- Sydonay: HECATE.
- WHAT...AM I DOING?
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
I'M SURE I'VE
FORGOTTEN SOMETHING.
- THESE ARE...
THE MEMORIES OF THE MYSTES.
- MY MEMORIES?
- YES, YOUR MEMORIES
ARE FLOWING INTO ME.
- MY, THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY'RE MINE.
- SHANA, DECIDE FOR YOURSELF
WHAT PATH YOU WISH TO TAKE.
- YEAH.
- Yuji: I KNOW HER.
THAT'S...
- YUJI.
- SHANA!
- WELL THEN,
ARE YOU INDEED READY?
- YEAH.
- ONCE WE STORM IN THERE, THERE
WILL INDEED BE NO TURNING BACK.
- I KNOW.
- AND OUR OBJECTIVE?
- Shana: THE ONLY
THING I'M CERTAIN OF
IS THAT I HAVE TO GO IN THERE.
- I UNDERSTAND.
IF WE GO, I'M SURE THE ANSWER
WILL BECOME CLEAR,
- BECAUSE YOU ARE A FLAME HAZE.
- YEAH.
- Tiamat: ENTER.
- SHANA. SHE PROTECTED ME,
EVEN THOUGH I'M NOTHING
BUT A MYSTES.
WHY?
- ( sighs )
I'M BECOMING FULFILLED...
WITH A MYSTES...
WITH A PERSON.
THOUGHTS DEEP AND STRONG.
I'VE NEVER CONTACTED
SOMETHING LIKE THIS BEFORE.
- SHANA.
- Shana: YUJI, I CAN FEEL YOU.
- THEY'RE COMING.
- OH, YES. I'M READY FOR THEM.
BUT WILL THEY EVEN
MAKE IT THIS FAR?
- SAKAI, YUKARI.
- HIRAI.
- COME ON.
- WHY ARE THERE SO MANY
DENIZENS FROM BALL MASQUE
HANGING AROUND HERE?
DO YOU THINK THE PALACE OF STARS
KICKED 'EM OUT?
- Marco: THEY SAY THE RATS ARE
THE FIRST TO FLEE
A SINKING SHIP.
- Margery: HA, THAT THING'S
BASICALLY UNSINKABLE.
ESPECIALLY WITH
THAT HAG, BEL PEOL, IN CHARGE.
BUT, THERE IS SOMETHING
STRANGE GOING ON
- Marco: THESE GUYS MAY BE
ABLE TO ANSWER A FEW QUESTIONS.
- ( chuckles ) THEN LET'S
START ASKING, SHALL WE?
FIRST, I'LL SOFTEN 'EM UP.
THAT'LL HELP 'EM START TALKING.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: SHANA AND WIRHELMINA
ENTER THE PALACE OF STARS
WHERE THEY FALL INTO THE TRAP
BALL MASQUE SET FOR THEM.
THE FINAL BATTLE, FROM WHICH
THERE IS NO TURNING BACK,
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
NEXT EPISODE,
"BATTLE AT THE PALACE OF STARS."