[Yu] So do your time leap
and change this world for us.
[Kumagami] Just make sure
to time it right...
[Shichino] Take my power
of permeation.
[Shunsake]
Been a while, little bro.
[Yu] I'm leaving the rest
up to you, Big Brother.
‐Uggh!
‐[teakettle whistling]
Huh?
Hey, might as well stay in bed.
We already did your job
and made food.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[young Yu] Jeez, we have rules
for a reason.
You better make breakfast
tomorrow, all right?
[young Shunsuke, Yu, and Ayumi]
Let's dig in!
Hey, Ayumi, how old are you
again, now?
I'm eight, of course.
[Shunsuke thinking]
That means we get captured
around three years from now.
After I made the time leap,
I started by becoming friends
with Kumagami and his group.
That way we could fight
together,
like we had promised,
in the future.
Kumagami was the one
that found me.
[Kumagami] That's an amazing
ability you've got.
Jeez, about time you showed up.
Huh? What are you talking about?
We were best friends.
We swore that we would
change the world together.
And I'm here to make sure
that we do!
Stay back,
don't come any closer!
[Shunsake] Waaah! [laughs]
[thud!]
[Kumagami moans]
What in the world are you?
Come on, you know
what my ability is.
Put two and two together
and take a guess.
‐Can it be that we met
in the future?
‐Yeah, you got it!
[Kumagami] Hey, we may know
each other in the future,
but for now we're strangers.
Don't get all chummy on me.
Jeez, you're such
a drag here, Pooh.
Pooh?
I call you Pooh
after that red‐shirted bear.
No way. I'd never let someone
call me a nickname
that stupid.
[chuckles]
[Shunsake] At that point,
Kumagami had already made
a small group
of ability wielders.
I followed him
to their safehouse
and met with
the fledgling group
as I had originally planned.
This is the one
who can time‐leap.
Shunsuke Otosaka.
It's been a while.
At least that's the way
it's been for me, not you.
Apparently he knows us.
He recently came here
from the future.
You really expect us
to believe that crap?
‐[Shunsake] You're Shichino.
‐Huh?
The wielder of permeation,
the ability to pass
through matter.
Unfortunately, passing through
even one wall
‐makes you feel like you
just ran a marathon.
‐[Shichino] What?
‐[Shunsake] Next Medoki.
‐Huh?
[Shunsake] You possess powers
of hypnotism.
You can make someone
fall asleep, but you also
fall asleep afterwards.
‐[Shunsake] Then Maedomari.
‐Yes.
[Shunsake] Able to erase
a memory from someone
with pinpoint accuracy.
However, for it to work,
you have to touch the target.
And it takes you a long time
to find that memory.
‐How's that?
‐[Maedomari] Amazing.
You're spot on.
That doesn't prove anything.
Kumagami could have
told you all that.
But that would mean Kumagami
is someone we can't trust.
Are you cool with that?
So, since you came
from the future,
you obviously want
something from us.
Yeah. Let me explain.
[Shunsake] And so I told them
about the tragic future
everyone
with special powers faced,
about myself and about them,
and then about the plan that I
had made with Kumagami
in the future.
There was only one path
for us to take.
We need to find everyone
and protect ourselves.
And so we started
creating a syndicate
of ability wielders,
but in the end, it was just
a gathering of children.
No matter how many times
we started over, we weren't
able to protect ourselves.
What's worse,
there were members
that went out of control
‐and assaulted the lab facility
to save their friends.
‐[young Shichino] Damn it!
[young Kumagami]
We don't have enough power
to protect ourselves.
This wasn't something
children could take on
in the first place.
[young Maedomari]
What should we do?
[sighs]
We can get help
from some adults.
Adults? There's no way we can
trust them, and you know it.
They don't have any abilities.
How can they possibly understand
what we're going through?
Some of them used to have
abilities.
In fact, I know a few of them.
Don't you all think
it's at least worth a shot?
‐[Medoki] Well, if you say so.
‐[Maedomari] Let's try it out.
[Shichino groans]
So, what will we do, exactly,
Shunsuke?
Well, let me think
about it for a bit.
Pooh.
[Ayumi] Big Brother Shun,
we'd like to wish you
‐a happy 15th birthday!
‐[laughter]
[Shunsake]
I need to time‐leap soon
or I'll get caught.
[announcer] Get ready for
the Mega Jumbo Fortune Lottery!
Our number‐one prize is...
600 million!
[Shunsake] Six‐hundred?
If we had that kind of money,
we could easily sway
some adults.
But why stop there?
If I use my ability...
This is it.
This is the only way left.
‐We need funding.
‐Oh?
I'll leap back to the past
and gather all sorts
of gambling information
like horse‐racing and lotto.
‐Nice.
‐And after that?
We'll gather even more wielders
and create a syndicate
the scientists
can never touch.
So we have to follow
this guy's orders again?
Come on, just give him a chance.
Well, see ya yesterday.
I just wish I didn't have to
explain all this again.
Arrggh.
[Shunsake] The morning
that I made the time leap,
I noticed something wrong
when I looked in the mirror.
This ability takes a bit
of vision away from me
each time I use it.
Since then, we added
all sorts of comrades
and created a plan for us to
gather a large sum of money.
It took many tries
and many time leaps.
My vision gradually
started to fail.
My ability takes in the light
off of every object,
every person, everything I see,
and uses it to take me
into the past.
If I went blind, I wouldn't
be able to use it again.
But I knew the risk.
[Kumagami] The research facility
was one step ahead of us again.
How many times
has this happened?
It's getting more frequent.
At this point, we're fighting
over ability wielders.
Shunsuke, we need a place
to keep them safe,
not to hide them.
Yeah. Give me a little time
to think up a plan... Pooh.
[Shunsake] How many times
have I experienced this?
An environment
where I can protect them.
Is there such a thing?
By the way, entrance exams
are coming up for you.
Have you picked
a high school yet?
[Shunsake] Hey, now,
there's an idea.
You! You are a freaking genius,
you know that?
Great, now will you
let me breathe?
[Shunsake] I'm going to leap
one more time, Pooh.
‐[Kumagami] Why?
‐I created a syndicate
and gained funding.
And yet I haven't been able
to protect everyone.
But you can't.
You know what'll happen.
Of course I do.
One more time leap
and my eyesight
is as good as gone,
but I have to take this chance.
You'll only get one shot,
so what are you planning
to do, exactly?
Create a school.
Why a school?
I've said it many times.
Our abilities disappear
once we're past adolescence.
If we build a school for them,
we can protect ability wielders
until they reach adulthood.
That way, I can protect
the potential ones
like you and Ayumi.
[Kumagami] I see, but this will
truly be your last gamble.
And it will cost you
your eyesight.
I know, but I'll live with it.
Of course you will.
You haven't changed one bit.
[Shunsake, chuckling] Please
make sure to find me after I've
gone completely blind.
[Kumagami] Leave that to me.
[Shunsake] I made
my very last time leap.
I haven't seen light since.
From that point on, I walked
down the ultimate path
in darkness.
But not alone.
For the final touch,
we decided to buy out
a certain educational
institution.
It was a pretty tiresome job.
But the joy everyone felt
once it was over
made it all worth it.
Now, something can be made
of this, right?
Yeah. You really came through
on this, thank you.
But this is just
the beginning.
I know that.
On that note, Pooh, I have
two favors to ask of you.
‐Go ahead.
‐First order of business.
I want you to erase
my existence
from you and Ayumi's memories.
‐Why?
‐If that doesn't happen,
there's no way I'll be able
to move around freely
from here on out.
I can no longer
live in the open. Forever.
I must keep living
behind the scenes.
‐Oh, I see.
‐Second.
I want you to create similar
syndicates all over Japan
and build more schools that can
harbor those with abilities.
Hadn't thought of that.
Even if we can't reach them
from here,
it's still our duty
to protect them.
But if I do that, my face
will be known all over
and it will become
dangerous for me.
[laughs] Well,
if that's the case,
how about you hide your face
with that long hair of yours?
Good idea. A little water
on top would make it perfect.
Uh‐huh.
Did you really
just drench yourself?
[Kumagami] Sure did.
[both laugh]
[young Shunsuke] I'm back.
Where have you been?
I've been worried sick
about you!
You could have tried
to give us a call.
I'm sorry. I brought a friend.
Is it cool if she comes in
for a bit?
This place is a mess!
Hold on!
‐Medoki, go do it.
‐[Ayumi] Where should I start?
‐[Medoki] Ayumi?
‐Oh, yes?
[Yu] Ayumi? Who is it?
[sighs]
[thud!]
Thank you.
‐Maedomari.
‐Yes.
[sighs] There, it's over.
I owe you one.
[Shunsake] Your future should be
fine from here on.
Live your lives peacefully.
I'll always love you,
no matter what.
‐All right, shall we?
‐Yes, sir.
‐Sure.
[Shunsake] And so I left,
completely vanishing
from Yu and Ayumi's lives.
And that's the end.
So you created this school
we've all become a part of
by time‐leaping repeatedly.
Wow!
[Shunsake] I'm sorry we didn't
make it in time to help
your big brother, Nao.
No. He's well on his way
to recovery right now.
It's all right.
You erased my memories of you
using an ability?
Yep, that's how it all
went down.
[Yu] You even lost
your eyesight.
I tried to leap again,
but it just wasn't happening.
There is something I still
have left undone.
I believe that
Kumagami mentioned it to you.
A promise the two of us
need to fulfill.
Ayumi. He said that we
could save her.
But you can't see.
You have to make
my time leap your own.
Use that ability of yours
and presto.
Plunder, right?
I've dreamt about it.
Taking abilities
is your true power.
And it's our only chance
to save Ayumi.
I never knew that.
‐[Tomori] Takajo and I knew
the whole time.
‐Huh?
Kumagami saw through
your ability.
It's kind of his thing,
you know.
His ability is the plunder
of other abilities.
Crazy! I can't believe that kind
of power is even real.
It's way too powerful.
We need to investigate
how he does it
before we go in guns blazing.
Good idea.
[Tomori] We'll have to keep
our guard up at all times.
As a result
of our investigation,
we realized that you had
misunderstood
the true nature
of your ability.
It's not that you are
merely possessing them.
The method by which
you plunder abilities
is by possessing wielders.
As proof of that, everyone
you've possessed up till now
has lost their powers.
You're saying that we could have
avoided a lot of crap
from the get‐go.
I could have possessed
the target outright?
Then everything
would have been fine?
Even for ability wielders,
that kind of treatment
violates human ethics.
We figured it would be better
for everyone concerned
if you understood why you
shouldn’t use your ability
carelessly.
Also, we were afraid
that you would have become
a dangerous threat
if you kept gaining
more power through plundering.
It was fortunate you didn't
realize this until now.
Very impressive.
I knew I liked you.
Then I can...
Ugggh!
My ability itself
should not have been lost, Yu.
Plunder that so you can
leap into the past
and save our sister.
All right, you should jump
to the day
that Ayumi develops
her ability.
Once you get there, plunder
collapse from her ASAP.
That should make it
safe for her.
Afterwards,
find me in the past
and fill me in
on everything that's going on.
You got all that?
[Yu thinking]
Ayumi, I'll save you.
‐[Yu] All right.
‐Good.
Then I'm counting on you.
I'm leaving the rest to you,
bro.
Don't worry,
I won't mess this up.
Now go!
Ehh! [gasp]
Ayumi!
What is today's date?
Yes, right where I need to be.
[thud!]
The ability is collapse.
‐[Yu] Here we go.
‐[Takajo]Any idea
what that is?
No. My guess is they can destroy
anything they target.
‐[Tomori] Where's this guy?
‐This is our condo complex.
‐[Yu] Can I have a minute?
‐[Tomori] What is it?
It's probably my little sister.
‐What’s your basis for that?
‐[Yu] She’s absent from school
with a cold.
To be at home at this time
of day
means it has to be
my little sister.
You're unusually sharp.
It's uncharacteristic.
Well, none of us are scientists,
but still...
I say we visit her.
That way we can see
if she's actually turned
into the wielder
of a special ability.
Wait, won't it seem
a little strange if we all
show up at once?
Tomori, it should just
be you and me.
That makes sense.
You're right.
You're right indeed.
Let's do that.
‐Hmm?
[Nomura] Come on,
it's time to go home!
Ayucchi, get better soon, 'K?
I'm sorry for being
so rowdy just then, sir!
[Yu] So it was her.
Anyway,
I'll get out of your hair.
Get well soon, kiddo.
[Ayumi] Thanks for coming.
I hope to see you again soon.
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐I'm gonna go see her off.
Back in a bit.
Whoo‐hoo‐hoo!
No.
[Tomori] Please ask her
what the nightmare was about.
It might be a clue
to figuring out
what the collapse ability is.
[Yu] Hey, Tomori,
if I told you that
I had time‐leaped here
from the future,
what would you think?
I would believe you.
If it was for Ayumi's sake,
you'd do something
just like that.
I have no doubt.
Good. Awesome.
That saves a lot of trouble.
In two days, Ayumi will die
when collapse goes
out of control.
I used a time leap so I could
come back here
and prevent that
from even happening.
[Tomori] So that's how it is.
I'm worried about you
doing this on your own,
so the student council
will help you.
That's great, thanks.
‐[Yu] You know...
‐[Tomori] Yes?
[Yu] I think I may have
completely misunderstood you.
After I lost Ayumi,
I became reckless
and nearly went to pieces.
I fell down a dark pit,
but then you came
and pulled me out.
[Tomori] Since you're talking
about the future,
I don't recall any of this,
but if you say that's
how it happened,
I guess it's true.
[Yu] I saw all sorts of
horrible things,
but you always knew
what to do.
[Tomori] Sure.
[Yu] Thank you.
[Tomori] Well... you're welcome.
I guess it's time
for bed again, isn't it?
No, not just yet.
‐Let me cast a magic spell
that can cure your cold.
‐Sure.
[Yu] How do you feel?
Pretty good.
Thanks, big brother.
[Yu] Ayumi's ability
is no longer with her.
One more thing to do.
[bell chiming]
[Yu] See ya. I'll come
pick you up to go home.
You're still recovering
so don't overdo it.
Right. I'll do
my very best, sir.
[Yu] This is the hard part.
I'll need to be careful.
[Tomori] Good morning.
[organ plays "Charge!"]
[Yu gasps]
I can't believe you got ahold
of those things.
And what are you
supposed to be?
They decided that no matter
what I did,
I wouldn't look like
a middle‐school student.
So I'm disguised
as a teacher.
[Tomori] Are you sure you
shouldn't have a disguise?
Hell yeah.
I want her to know
it was Ayumi's big brother
that showed up.
Good idea. That totally changes
how formidable you look.
Hmm. Everyone,
I'm counting on you.
Right. We'll make sure
to save your sister's life.
‐After that, we party! Yeah!
‐Yeah!
By the way, there isn't
a magic spell for
saving someone's life.
‐I'm sorry.
‐Now, over here.
We'll go in from
the back entrance.
[Yusa] Oh!
[man] Hey, are you a student
of this school?
[Takajo] Uh, I'm a teacher here.
Is there some kind of problem?
I don't recognize you at all.
Let's go to the faculty office.
[Takajo] Well, sure, I'll go.
After all, I am a teacher.
[Yu] I've already
freakin' lost one!
At least I still have
Tomori and Yusa.
[boy] Whoa. Hey,
you're Yusarin, aren't you?
No, I'm totally not.
[boy] I knew it.
You are her!
Everyone, Yusarin,
the famous idol, just
transferred to our school!
[students cheering, shrieking]
[girl] She's prettier
than on TV.
[Misa] Grrr! I ain't nothing
like Yusarin!
So you're saying you aren't like
how you act on TV?
‐Ah, for the love of crap.
‐[spits]
Would a pop idol
do something like this?
‐[boy] What should I do
with this saliva?
‐[Tomori] So creepy!
Hey, this other new girl
is pretty cute, too.
Maybe she's an idol
like Yusarin.
[girl] They could be filming
a secret show right now.
[boy] Wait, I thought
Yusarin was in high school.
You damn traitor!
Don't leave me here
by myself!
[Yu]
They were caught instantly.
What was the point
of wearing disguises?
[girls shrieking,
footsteps thundering]
[Yu] One hour left.
[tires squeal]
[Konishi] It's all because
you showed up.
[gasp] Oikawa! It's like he's
completely forgotten about me.
He just looks at you
all the time!
[gasping]
[Ayumi gasps]
[Konishi] It's all your fault.
It's all your fault.
[blade clicking]
‐It's all your fault!
‐No, that's not true!
That's why I'll make you
feel pain for a change!
[gasp] Who are you?
Big Brother Yu?
I'm gonna have to scare you
a bit.
[shrieks]
What's happening?
[Yu] The next time you try
to harm my little sister,
you won't get off this easily.
Get lost before I get mad!
[screams]
I was so scared!
I'm so glad you're safe.
Let's go home for today.
‐Sound good to you?
‐Uh‐huh. Yeah.
[Yu] I saved her.
I was able to save her.
We actually did it.
I don't care if people say
I have a sister complex.
I never want to lose
Ayumi again.
You're already here, Kumagami?
That was fast.
Huh? Hold on.
You already know about me?
That's right, Pooh.
That makes it easy.
Come with me,
you and your little sister.
Sure thing. Take us to him.
To our big brother.
[woman singing in Japanese]