[raining]
[gasp] Doctor!
Doctor!
[running footsteps]
How are you feeling?
[gasp] Ayumi. My little sister!
[doctor] I'm terribly sorry.
She didn't make it.
I'm Detective Someda.
I'm terribly sorry
for your loss.
I'd like to work with you
so we can figure out what really
happened at the school.
I heard that you
were at the scene...
[woman] Are you all right?
I'm sure this has been
rough for you.
But for her sake,
you have to keep moving forward
with your life, you understand?
There are many things
in this world that time solves.
But it won't solve everything.
[bells chime]
[Yu] Did... did I do...
even one thing for her?
Was I able... to repay her?
[gasp] No. I didn't repay her
at all.
[sobbing] Nothing.
I never thought she could
be gone this quickly.
It just didn't seem possible.
Even if I wanted to repay,
I couldn't.
I'll never get another chance.
[sobbing]
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
[Yu thinking]
Was there anything left?
‐[man on TV] The love letters
just keep pouring in.
[woman] In your dreams, maybe.
Be honest.
The last piece
of fan mail you got was from
your mother, wasn't it?
[man] Actually,
she sent hate mail.
[woman] Accepting enrollment
at Shinkou Seminars now.
[man] Let's move on.
The flavor of
instant noodles‐‐
[contestant] Uh, yuzu pepper!
‐[doorbell rings]
‐[man] Correct!
‐[man] The entire question
was this:
The flavor of instant noodles,
what is the best ingredient
that can be added
to enhance the flavor?
[doorbell rings]
[Yusa] Otosaka!
Otosaka, if you haven't
eaten yet, would you like
to have dinner with us?
I brought some.
It's my special homemade
cream stew.
[Takajo] Come on, you can't
turn down something like that.
[Yu] I don't want any.
[Yusa] Well, what should we do?
[Takajo] Let's look again.
[Takajo sighs]
Darn it,
I think he went back already.
[snarls]
[shrieks]
It was going to be mine!
Now Yusarin's cream stew
is ruined!
[Misa] You creeper! Look,
I'll have Yusa make you
as much as you want.
All you have to do is break
the door with your ability.
I can break fortified glass,
sure, but this door
is too thick.
Due to security reasons,
it's made a lot sturdier
than normal condos.
[sighs] You're so damn useless.
[Takajo shrieks]
Even if I burn the door,
nothing will come of it.
I don't know what to do
in this situation.
I get what he must be
feeling now.
Hell, I know it a lot better
than most people.
[Yusa] Huh? What?
OK, so what happened here,
exactly?
It seems that he needs
a bit more time to heal.
I see. Then let's come back
again later.
[doorbell rings]
[ring]
[man] Between the top six
baseball teams...
[door opens]
[girl] Excuse me.
Sorry to barge in
without permission.
[man] The current champs,
the Giants...
[tap on door]
It's me, Shirayanagi.
[cup crumples]
[man] ... with the hope
that this would reverse their
current state of emergency.
[landlord] Is he all right?
Yes. He seems OK to me.
[landlord] All right,
I'll leave him to you, then.
‐[door closes]
‐Who is it?
You saved me from a truck
when we were classmates once.
[Yu] Oh.
So?
I heard that you haven't been
to school ever since...
About your little sister,
I'm terribly sorry.
I'm in no position
to say this, but...
is there anything I can do?
[Yu] No.
[Shirayanagi] Anything is fine.
Please, Otosaka,
I just want to help you,
if you'll let me.
Help me? What makes you think
that I need any help?
I'm totally fine.
There's no way that's true.
I mean, you've been eating
nothing but instant noodles.
[Yu] I like them,
so it's OK.
[Shirayanagi] Well, then...
how about those pancakes
we had together?
We could get them again.
Pancakes?
When did we eat that?
The day you saved me.
Oh. Instant noodles
or pancakes.
Aren't they about
the same nutrition‐wise?
[Shirayanagi] Yeah,
I suppose you're right.
But we could still go outside.
[Yu] Right.
Uh... I'm glad.
[Yu] Can you get me
more instant noodles
while you're out?
Huh?
You’re running an errand
for me, aren’t you?
Instant noodles.
I don't care what kind.
[Shirayanagi] No, no.
Otosaka, you're coming with me.
I don't feel like it.
I'll pay you back later, OK?
I won't go unless you do.
[Yu] You won't go
unless I go, huh?
Shirayanagi, was it?
Are you my legal guardian now?
No, I don't mean it
like that at all.
But I am concerned
for you right now.
‐[Yu] So you won't do it?
‐No, I won't!
Look, Otosaka, it's important
that you get outside a bit.
If you stay cooped up, you'll
only drive yourself insane.
‐Like mentally ill?
‐Yes.
There's no chance
of that at all.
I told you, I'm totally fine.
If you were, you wouldn't be
living like this.
It just proves
that you're depressed.
[Yu sighs]
[Yu] Who do you think
you are?!
I never asked you
to come here!
If you're not going to run
errands for me, you can leave.
OK, I'll go.
I shouldn't have come here.
I'm sorry.
[sports commentary
in background]
[Yu] I better stock up again.
[doorbell rings]
[ring]
[Yu thinking] I guess they're
here to capture me by force.
Shirayanagi may have been
acting because she was asked to,
which means
it's time to make my exit.
Ugggh!
[thud, scream]
I'll be out for a while.
[beeping]
[Yu thinking]
If I have this much,
I'm sure I can live for a while
without going back home.
I need to go somewhere
far away
so that soggy freak show
can't locate me.
This might be far enough
for now.
I'm sick of noodles, so I guess
I'll have some pizza.
Whaddya know?
I gave them the slip.
[woman] Excuse me.
Your pizza and a salad.
Salad? Must be a free item.
I'll pass.
[sighs]
So damn boring.
How many days has it been?
Nothing has gone on
for this long.
I'm sure they won't find me.
‐[footsteps]
‐I guess.
I'll go out
for just a little bit.
[sighs]
Hmm.
‐[Yu] Can I have that?
‐[vendor] Sure thing.
It's good.
It's been a while since I had
something sweet.
‐[boy 1] Watch your left.
Your left!
‐[boy 2] I got it!
[boy 1] Kick ass!
[Yu] Huh.
Never seen a game like that.
[dramatic soundtrack plays]
Huh. Ahh...
[chuckles]
Now, this is fun!
[hysterical laughter]
Die! Die!
I'll kill every single one
of you who gets in my way!
‐[hysterical laughter]
‐Die! I want you to die!
[game music plays,
gunfire sfx]
[boy] Eat my lead
and like it!
[both chuckling]
‐Take this! Boo‐yah!
‐[explosion sfx]
[Yu] You've been playing
for hours.
Get outta the way!
The hell. What'd you say?
Trying to pick a fight?
What's up?
This punk hit me with trash
and told me to move.
[boy 2] Who do you think
you are, kid?
[Yu] Just a normal,
law‐abiding citizen.
A law‐abiding citizen that
assaults people with trash?
‐Yeah, it looked good on you.
‐Don’t mock us!
[man] Take him outside.
[train clanging]
Just remember,
you asked for this.
Ready for some pain,
hot‐shot?
Huh? You think you can beat me?
[chuckles] Bring it.
I'll make sure you can't play
games for a while.
Hmm.
You bastard!
What do you think you're doing?
Huh? What the hell,
I thought I punched this guy!
What's wrong?
You guys have a falling out?
Kiss and make up.
‐Hyah!
‐Uggh!
What is this?
What the hell is going on?
Ugggh!
[screams]
I still have one more left.
No, stop, stop!
[screams]
[Yu] Now you know
how strong I am.
Next time you go against me,
I won't hesitate to kill you.
Got it? [chuckles]
Yo. How's it going?
You're the punk that beat
Gondo's gang all by himself?
Maybe. It's not like I stopped
to ask their names, you know.
Well, I'm Hosoyamada.
Remember that.
[Yu] I give it five seconds
before I forget all about you.
[Hosoyamada] You've got
some balls, kid.
You should really learn
some respect.
Give him his first lesson, boys.
What the hell are you doing?
Ugggh!
It wasn't me!
You don't need this eye, right?
If I take it, you can call
yourself something cool
like "One‐Eyed‐Hoso‐whatever."
You don't seem excited.
What's wrong,
don't like the name?
[singsong] Better choose!
Fine! I give! Mercy!
[bystander] The Hosoyamada lost?
[bystander 2] Impossible.
[shouts, groans]
Nobody can win against me.
‐[chuckles]
‐[thunder rumbles]
[Yu thinking] Real fights
are tons more fun
than a stupid game.
Hmm?
[straining]
What is this thing?
Something important to you?
So that's how it is.
[whoosh!]
Hey wait...
When did... when did you...?
[Tomori] The whole time.
[Yu] The whole time?
It can't be.
If you keep following
this path,
you'll lose your humanity
and never get it back again.
That's why I stopped you.
Did somebody send you?
No. I'm on a leave of absence
for now.
‐This is personal.
‐How so?
I feel responsible for this
as well.
When you get down to it,
I might have made a bad call
concerning Ayumi.
Maybe I should have
quarantined her immediately.
At least then
she would have been safe.
That's why I've decided
to stick with you
until this is through
and you're back to normal.
This is none of your business!
You owe me for that stuff!
Do you want to be done
with your life?
Do you want to stop
being human?
Then...
what am I supposed to do?
Hmm.
A fresh change of clothes
would be a nice start.
‐But let's get some food
for now.
‐Huh?
A good meal is the foundation
of a healthy mood and lifestyle.
There's nothing wrong
with what I've been eating.
Right, a diet of pizza
and sweat soy sauce mochi
is so healthy.
It'll calm you down,
at least.
What are you saying
I should eat?
[Tomori] You just leave it
to me.
I'll get it for you right away.
Hey, it's me. Yes.
Thank you very much.
I didn't say for you to set
something up for me!
Just take one bite.
After that, I swear
we will have nothing to do
with each other again.
Just one bite, huh?
Then you'll leave me alone
forever?
[Tomori] Yes, I promise.
[Yu] Fine.
[Tomori] Good, then let's go.
‐[Yu] That promise is absolute?
‐[Tomori] Right.
‐Takajo?
‐[Tomori] Yes. His family home.
[Yu] Is this
an ambush or something?
[Tomori] Nobody is here
so you can relax.
Watch some TV or something.
[Yu] What are you making me eat?
[Tomori] That's a surprise
for you to see
when it's finished.
‐I didn't know
she was allergic.
‐Are you stupid?
‐[man 1] It was
a poison mushroom, idiot!
‐[man 2] Nuh‐uh.
[man 2] It grew naturally,
out of the ground.
It couldn't be poison.
[chopping vegetables]
‐[Tomori and Ayumi]
Here, it's done!
‐[Yu gasps]
Here you go.
It's the same taste.
‐Glad I did it justice.
‐[Yu] How?
Your mother left behind
a big notebook full of recipes.
I took the liberty
of borrowing it.
The page with the omelet rice
was the only one
with a big, flowery circle
on it.
I have a feeling
it was your favorite food
when you were a kid.
After your mother
was no longer around,
I think Ayumi saw that
and tried to recreate the taste
to make you happy.
[Yu] So that was...
the last omelet rice.
Damn it.
It's sweet
and it tastes so horrible.
Why am I eating it?
It's not healthy for you
to scarf it down like that.
Just eat slowly and savor it.
[Yu] OK.
[Tomori] Here. Have some tea.
And take this, too.
‐Hey, Tomori.
‐[Tomori] Yes?
What the hell am I supposed
to do with myself now?
Well, you could always return
to the student council
and help us out.
[Yu] But that's not possible.
We promised we would never have
anything to do with each other.
Huh? What the heck
are you talking about?
[Yu] You said that's what would
happen after I ate this.
Yeah, if you ate one bite,
but you scarfed it down
like a hungry stray.
"Oh, wow, he must really
wanna stay with me!" [laughs]
That's what I kept thinking,
at least.
[theme song plays]
Of course you did.
All right.
Student council it is.
I'm glad to hear it.
[woman singing in Japanese]