[jet taking off]
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
What's the purpose
of your visit?
[Yu] Well, um...
sightseeing.
Very well then.
Enjoy your stay.
Uh... please, sir, the list.
[groans]
[Yu] I need to find someone
with a search ability first.
Guess I'll ask their leader.
It's got to be this one.
Now, what kind of ability
will he have?
‐[alarm chirps]
‐This guy?
[gasp]
Oh!
Let's see now.
If you move,
you get roasted.
‐You the leader?
‐Who are you?
Hang on.
An ability wielder,
just like you.
[man] Huh? How come
I can't read his mind?
One sec.
‐"How come I can't
read his mind?"
‐[gasp]
[man] He stole my ability?
Oh, let's see.
That's right.
[Yu] This really
is a useful ability.
I got a question.
How are you locating other
ability wielders? Tell me!
[man] Don’t think, don't think!
Don't think!
Angelo? Cool. Guess I'll be
paying him a visit next.
Thanks a lot, buddy.
[chuckles]
‐Damn you to...
‐[thud!]
You crashed my ride.
Not cool, man.
Let me out of here!
[kids laughing]
Huh?
[gasp]
‐What?
‐Are you Angelo?
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
Your ability
is an illness, OK?
You don't have to use it
anymore.
Huh?
Impossible.
Good to know. You just have
to look at the map.
Amazing.
His ability to find
wielders is perfect.
Hmm.
[reporter]
Earlier this morning,
‐[explosion]
‐the UN announced that
the Democratic
Revolutionary Army...
[Yu] That hurt!
Uggh!
...had been subjugated.
The UN Chairman,
Brian Jackson, reported
that a young man suspected
to be the ringleader
and several others have been
apprehended unhurt...
I guess my work
really is paying off.
..."I hope there will be
a quick, peaceful resolution."
[Yu] It looks like
there are other places
that are gathering
ability wielders.
[groans]
It's...
It's the One‐Eyed Grim Reaper!
Jeez, that's an
embarrassing nickname.
Couldn't they have come up
with something cooler?
I mean, come on!
[crackling]
[Yu] What was that image?
Weird.
Whoa! Oh.
I guess I'm able to learn
what the plundered ability is
without knowing it now.
I've plundered all the abilities
of yet another country.
And guess what?
I understand every single
language in the world now.
And if I decide
I don't want to,
I never need
to sleep again.
[Shunsake] Oh, that's amazing.
But don't overexert yourself
too much.
No. I have to hit the next
country ASAP.
Time's precious.
[Shunsake] You're right.
I know this is rough,
but I'm counting on you
to finish this before
you lose your powers.
[Yu] Yeah.
[man screaming]
[sighs]
[Yu] This one
makes illnesses worse?
[Yu] They’re all clumped
together again.
How can they do that
to children?
Huh? That clump
only has one glimmer.
What does that mean?
[whoosh!]
What the...?
No images are popping up.
What kind of a facility
is this?
[man straining]
Carriers?
Aha. So that's what this means.
I get it.
They've been infected,
but their abilities
haven't broken out yet,
so they're just carriers.
Darn it, I can't plunder
what isn't there.
What should I do?
Yes, these special abilities
are indeed a disease.
So before particles are spread
all over Earth again,
we need to vaccinate
every person in the world.
[Yu] That's right.
If it's an illness,
I can make it worse,
and the ability should
break out.
Wouldn't that make it
plunderable?
All right, that went well.
I'll have to plunder from
all carriers from now on, too.
Otherwise new wielders
could pop up right after
I leave a country.
[machine‐guns rattle and fire]
Shoot until you're out of ammo!
[Yu] Arrggh!
Oh! Ha ha.
Gracias. Is much better.
[Yu] So there's even someone
with an ability to heal.
I'm sorry. Even if you're using
your ability for good,
I can't allow you to keep it.
This hand...
if I put it up to my eye,
then...
I can have full sight
and use my time leap again.
I might even be able
to save Kumagami.
No way.
I didn't plunder abilities
for something like that.
From now on, I will not allow
for acts that break
human reason.
I'll rid this world
of abilities.
And that is my only purpose now.
[phone rings]
[confused voices echo]
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
[screaming]
[busy signal]
Hey, are you all right, man?
‐[Yu] Are you the enemy?
‐Huh?
Don't play dumb.
Are you my enemy or not?!
[screams]
Please don't kill me!
[Yu] That's right.
Calm down. Calm down.
I shouldn't kill anyone.
[reporter] They have announced
that they have captured
Mayor Hassan Muscle
of their capital city.
So I'm going there tomorrow.
I should sleep,
if only for a little while.
It'll be good for me.
According
to government reports...
[Yu] It is necessary
to rest one's body
every so often.
[reporter] The government
has announced this morning
that the leader
of the coup d'état,
Mohsen bin Yazid,
has just agreed
to an unconditional surrender.
‐The ongoing battle continued
within the capital city...
‐What?
What the hell's going on?
[gasping] What?
...have suffered
major damage.
Did I make this happen?
This isn’t good.
My memory’s starting
to get muddled.
I shouldn't sleep after all.
[Yu] What in the world
am I doing here?
Why am I in a battlefield?
[snarls]
What is this?
That's right.
I made a promise...
that I would plunder every last
ability in the world
and then come back to her.
Back to her?
Who was she?
I'm sure she was someone
very dear to me.
But I can't remember.
♪
I see. Someone with
the explosion ability
will show up there.
[frightened muttering]
[man] You must be the Reaper
I keep hearing about.
All right, I will take you
with me, then!
Revolu...
Damn it!
That ability of yours only
brings death and misfortune.
[man] One‐Eyed?
Could you be the Reaper?
Yeah. The big, bad reaper!
[boom!]
Friendly neighborhood Reaper
here.
[man straining]
[boom!]
[Yu laughing hysterically]
This is too tough, man.
I don't wanna do this.
Who the hell made this plan,
and why do I have to do it?
I've practically visited every
corner of the damn world.
That's enough, isn't it?
I'm so tired of doing this crap
day in and day out.
Someone please take over
for me.
[chuckles] I know
what I can do.
I could just take over
the world with my powers.
It would be easy.
I'm a god!
Everyone will fall in line!
Do as I say!
[hysterical laughter]
Huh?
What the hell is this?
Filthy garbage!
What’s going on?
Why do I feel angry at myself
for kicking this thing?
I don't get it.
I'm crying. What the hell
is happening to me?
What's up with this?
I still need to keep
doing my best.
[sniffling]
[gasping]
It's the Reaper!
[shrieking]
[gunshot]
Gimme that!
[guard] Why won't
any of it hit?
Is that kid some kind of demon?!
Worse. He's the One‐Eyed
Grim Reaper!
‐We can't win.
‐Out of my way!
[kids screaming]
Say goodbye to the boogieman.
You're kidding me!
That was an RPG.
[snarls]
‐[boy 1] You saved us.
‐[girl] Thank you so much.
‐[boy 2] We appreciate it.
[gasps]
[screams]
[Yu] It's close to here.
I did it! Ha ha ha!
I finally got
the One‐Eyed Reaper!
Huh?
You shouldn't pick
on the weak, you bully!
Are you freakin' kiddin' me?
Do you have any idea
who that is, kid?
No clue, but still,
I won't let you hurt him!
That guy has a huge bounty
on his head.
If I nab him,
I get paid a king's ransom.
[girl]
Yeah, but it's still wrong!
All right, little girl,
if you want some pain,
I'll deliver.
Do whatever you want.
I will not stand aside, ever!
[snarls]
‐What the...?
‐[clang!]
[Yu] Of all things.
The very last ability wielder
in the whole world
had the power of courage in her.
But that kind of reckless valor
will get you killed someday.
‐Just go home now.
‐Huh?
You shouldn't...
You still have plenty of courage
without the power.
Run along now.
OK, but I'll go call for help.
I'll be back just as soon
as I can.
It's over.
I promised.
I need to get back.
It's all over.
So I need to get back.
I accomplished everything.
Get back... to where?
[thwack!]
[Yu muttering]
I need to get back.
I must have made...
a promise.
‐[man laughing]
‐Lap of luxury, here I come!
‐[helicopter hovering]
‐Huh?
What is that?
[Shunsake] Yu!
[woman singing
ballad in Japanese]
[sighs]
[Tomori] Took you long enough.
Thanks for all the hard work.
And for keeping
the promise we made.
[groans]
[Tomori] Your life
is not in danger,
but you should take some time
to rest properly.
[Yu] OK.
Oh, by the way, miss,
who are you?
[gasp]
So that's how things roll.
Of course it's understandable.
Since you plundered thousands,
tens of thousands of abilities,
the stress caused to your brain
must be staggering.
It's a blessing that you
can even talk.
My name's Tomori
and I am your lover.
A lover? But I don't
even recognize you.
[Tomori] That hurts, a lot more
than I expected.
I'm so sorry.
Did I make you sad just now?
Yeah, a little bit.
Because we were classmates
and worked together
in the student council.
And before you left,
you promised me that we
would be lovers.
Uh‐huh?
Sorry, I don't remember
any of that.
Huh?
[Tomori] These flash cards,
I made them for you,
so you held onto them
until the very end.
Did they come in handy?
So, these were a gift?
You made these?
Yes.
While I was traveling,
they were like
a good luck charm.
This was the one thing
I couldn't part with.
Even though it's so tattered
and half torn.
It means a lot.
Thanks for that.
[sobbing] If you were able
to come back like this
because of it,
I couldn't be any happier.
Did I make you sad again?
[Tomori] No. I'm just happy.
That's all.
I'm not sure I get it,
but please don't cry.
[Tomori] That's impossible.
Yu Otosaka,
I'm so glad you're back!
[woman singing in Japanese]
[Tomori] This is a camcorder
that I kept recording things
I didn't want
for the longest time.
But from now on, I will keep
recording all of you.
I will record lots and lots
of happy, everyday life.
That way, we can leave behind
lots and lots of happy memories.
‐Sounds good to me.
‐Yep.
Oh, can I be a part
of the memories, too?!
Of course.
Not sure what to say
right now.
Then just be honest.
I'm looking forward
to the future.
Yay! Let's make it a good one!
I'm so there!
From now on,
we'll make sure our lives
are filled with fun
and happiness.
[giggles]