Hyaa!
‐I'm gonna go.
‐[Ayumi] Wait a minute!
You're forgetting something!
‐Your lunch!
‐What's the menu today?
It's omelet rice, your favorite.
[Yu thinking] That again?!
[Yu] Th‐Thanks.
Now don't you be late, OK?
[Ayumi] I won't.
[Yu sighs]
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
Please excuse me.
[Tomori] Welcome
to our academy.
[snickers]
[Yu groans]
[Yu] So every single student
here has some special ability?
[Takajo] No. Some have
the possibility of having one,
and some show signs
of developing one.
[Yu] You transfer them here
just for that?
[Tomori] A long time ago,
people who had special
abilities like we have
could end up as guinea pigs
for misguided and sometimes
cruel neuroscientists.
If you got caught,
your life was basically over.
Hah! You're exaggerating.
[Tomori] I'm actually talking
about my big brother.
To protect those with abilities,
a certain individual created
the current system,
though not in time
to save my big brother.
So why did you get me
into this student council
and tell me I should
use my powers?
The student council here
is entrusted with
a special mission,
and that is to seek out those
with special abilities
who are on the loose,
like you were,
and either protect them
or threaten them
to never use their powers.
Why would I do
something like that?
[Tomori] In return,
you will be paid appropriately.
Isn't Ayumi having
to do her best to make
decent meals every day
because you can't even afford
to buy proper food?
My name is Yu Otosaka.
I came here
from Hinomori High School.
Nice to meet you all.
[girl, gasping] So cute!
[Yu snickers]
[gasp]
[Takajo chuckles]
[music on earphones]
Hey. She's a first‐year, but
she's student council president?
Right. In this academy,
the student council president
is not determined by grade.
It goes to someone who's active
and has a sense of duty
as someone
with a special ability.
[Yu] I see.
This is exactly the same thing
as last night's dinner.
Say, Otosaka, what are you going
to do about lunch today?
Well, I don't have anything.
[Takajo] Then let's go
to the cafeteria together.
I'll show you where it is.
That would be a big help.
You're not going
to invite her?
[Takajo] I can ask her
to come along if you like.
Nah. No thanks.
Doesn't seem to be
any open seats.
Then how about we buy
some sandwiches
and go back to the classroom
to eat?
[Yu] Well, it's pretty crowded
over there, too.
Just leave that part to me.
Here's where I can show off
my ability.
‐Is it OK for you to do that?
‐Don't worry, it's fine.
I'll go in from the blind spot
on the camera.
Though, since I'll be
going by too quickly,
what kind of breads I grab
will all depend on luck.
[Yu] Huh? [voice slows] Hey.
[drawn‐out shout]
[shout ends, students scream]
[sighs]
‐[boy] What was that?
‐[girl] An explosion?
[Takajo] Sorry to make you wait.
Oh, I got a rather great
result this time.
‐A cutlet sandwich.
‐What?
You call that a great result
with all those wounds on you?
I do wear armor
under my uniform
so the wounds are never
very deep, you know.
[Yu] But you're
bleeding from your head!
You know, you're
a pretty dangerous guy,
despite how you look.
What do you mean by that?
[Yu] Wait, you have nothing
but cutlet sandwiches here.
[Takajo, mouth full]
It's teleportation, you know.
You think I had time to pick
and choose what I wanted?
And every single one
of them is smushed.
That's teleportation.
You think I can fine‐tune
how forcefully I grab
merchandise
when I'm moving that fast?
[Yu] His ability
really is half‐assed.
She doesn't have
any female friends,
even though she's
the student council president?
Her special ability is to become
completely invisible
to one person she chooses.
Which means that everyone
other than that person
can see her.
That imperfection is
what caused the situation
she's in right now.
Even if she had a valid reason,
what would people
around her think
after seeing her use her ability
to take violent actions?
On top of that,
the surveillance cameras
show nothing
but an ordinary fight.
As she kept doing things
like that,
obviously people eventually
came to hate her.
But apparently her personality
wasn't like that
until she got
into middle school.
‐[footsteps]
‐Huh?
‐Oh. She's walking over here.
A helper will soon be
showing up.
‐What the hell?
‐That means, everyone gather
at the student council room.
Huh? How did you figure that?
[Yu] What in the world is about
to begin here?
[gasp] Who is this guy?
Thoughtography... right here.
[Yu] Huh?
Who was that?
A comrade who tells us
the location and power
of someone who possesses
a special ability.
Nanba High School,
We'll go stake it out.
‐Come on, we're leaving early.
‐[Yu] To do what?
Some investigation, of course.
Even though we're not
with the police?
If the police you mention
find this person before we do,
that person's life
is all but over.
[Yu] Seriously?
‐[Tomori] Start asking around.
‐[Takajo] Right!
Come on, now.
Let's get started.
What is it I should be doing?
Basically, ask whether
anything strange has been
going on lately.
Also, since the ability has been
determined to be thoughtography,
it might be good to ask about
any rumors that involve
photographs.
[Tomori] Very funny.
Good luck.
What am I doing?
Those two are nothing more
than a couple of lunatics.
[Tomori panting]
There was someone acting
suspicious.
I want you to take over
his body and look through
all of his belongings.
For what purpose?
To protect the one
with special abilities.
[Yu snarls]
[Tomori snarls]
Oh, fine. Which guy is it?
Damn it, you took so long,
I've lost him.
Follow me!
‐[Tomori] That's the guy.
‐[suspect whimpering]
‐Hurry!
‐[Yu] Damn it. Why do I have
to do something like this?
[groans]
Huh? Hey.
Whaaaa!
‐[suspect groans]
‐What's this? Whoa!
Hey, what are you
doing with that?
[Tomori] Pictures
of a female student.
She's rather pretty.
Next up, well, a girl
in her lingerie.
This is thoughtography?
You sure use it
for something stupid.
Did you take
either of these pictures?
No, no. I bought them.
Then who did you buy them from?
Look, I don't intend on leaking
any of what you tell me
to a third party, OK?
Please just tell me
the truth.
If you don't tell us now,
I'll tell the girl
in this photograph
that this was in your possession
and that you took it.
Udoh... in class 2‐E.
Thank you very much.
OK, we're going in.
We're gonna go capture Udoh
from 2‐E.
[Takajo] Right!
Huh?
Can you tell me if Udoh
has gone home yet?
[girl] Huh? No, Udoh is...
Captain, if I may excuse myself.
Yeah. Good work today.
[sighs]
‐Wow, this is a surprise.
‐[gasp]
‐Who are you?
Where did you come from?
‐[Tomori laughs]
[Tomori] Who would have thought
that the culprit
who takes lewd, perverted
photographs like this with
his thoughtography ability
and sells them off
to his classmates
is also the school's
archery team captain?
Photograph?
Thoughtography?
I don't know what you mean.
Forget it. One of your customers
gave you up.
Oh, yeah, we took a really good
look inside your locker, too.
A ton of photos came falling out
so I recorded them all
on this video camera
as evidence.
I can easily open something like
a locker inside a clubhouse.
Why would you do such a thing?
[Udoh] Because I can make money
with it, of course.
[Tomori] This involves
your family's finances?
Your parents wouldn't be happy
with you making money
like this, you know.
They're sick, OK?
There's nothing else I can do!
I projected you
in your underwear here.
It includes your face.
If you don't want this photo
distributed everywhere,
you'll forget this
ever happened.
[gasp]
That's all thoughtography takes?
I'm impressed.
But, um, no one
would ever need that.
[Udoh] No matter who looks
at you, you're attractive.
[gasp] Seriously?
I got a compliment!
All right!
Yeah, so hurry up
and get outta here.
Nice work.
The photo is... gone?
[Tomori] It's right here.
But wait, how did you...?
Oh, man!
That's checkmate.
Just give up, OK?
Pretend like none of this
ever happened.
You're the worst kind of person,
you know that?
So how much martial arts spirit
you possess means nothing!
[Takajo cries in slow motion]
[screams]
[gasps]
Just so you know,
we really don't plan
on handing you over
to the police
or anything like that.
However, if you keep
using those powers,
your life will be
completely ruined.
Do you want to become
an experimental subject
dissected by scientists?
‐Dissected?
‐So this is a warning.
Those powers will disappear
once your body is finished
with adolescence.
As for money, earn some
by working legitimate
part‐time jobs.
[Tomori] We took care of that
successfully.
[Takajo] Indeed, we did.
Tell me, you guys always
do things like this?
Yes. So that no one
with special abilities
ends up like my big brother.
I see. So what is it, exactly,
that actually happened
to your big brother
after he got
caught by the scientists?
[Tomori] It's not like
I'm hiding him or anything.
How about we visit tomorrow?
Huh? Visit where?
Where my big brother is now.
OK, are you ready to go?
Yeah. What about you?
I'm going to take a pass
this time.
Take care.
You haven't eaten lunch yet,
have you?
No.
Then let's buy station‐specific
lunches at the kiosk!
I want this one!
A beef‐tongue bento box lunch
that warms up
when you pull a string!
‐This is totally amazing!
‐Yeah, I know all about them.
[Yu] I can't believe it,
this is so embarrassing.
How can she eat like that
in a situation like this?
It's bad manners, no matter
how you look at it.
What's wrong?
Aren't you gonna eat
the sandwich you bought?
Ahhhhh...
[Tomori] My big brother
was the first to have
a special ability.
I'd just passed
the middle school entrance exams
for a national university
magnet school.
[footsteps]
[young Tomori] I did it, Mom!
I did it!
I got accepted!
You really did do
your best now.
That means you could
end up being a doctor,
or even a minister.
[Tomori] Yup!
Big Brother, look at this.
I got accepted.
Seriously? Unlike me,
you're completely amazing,
you know?
No, you're much more amazing
than me, Big Brother.
I heard that some of
the record companies
are starting to notice
what a great band you have.
Since we're poor, I want
to hurry up and land myself
a major record deal
so I can live on my own.
Hey, did you ever listen
to that CD I lent you?
It would get in the way
of my studies, so no, I haven't.
Your entrance exams
are over now so listen to it.
I want to create sounds
just like it and soar
to the top.
[Tomori]
I'm not really interested
in rock music and stuff.
[brother] It's different.
Zhiend is not rock music,
it's post‐rock.
[Tomori] You said that
before, too.
Like, I don't understand
what you mean at all.
As it turned out, I wasn't
able to enter that school.
I have something important
to say.
I've decided to enter you both
in a boarding school
so that each of you has
the chance to develop
your special talents.
‐Huh?
‐What do you mean?
I was just about to sign
to a record label.
I'm sorry,
but can't you put that off
for just a little while?
I don't get any of this!
If I can support myself,
that will take the pressure
off our money situation!
[mother] It's actually
the reverse.
We'll be better off financially
if you guys go to this school...
What do you mean, the reverse?
In the first place,
Nao is good at studying,
but I'm just an idiot who only
knows how to play the guitar!
[mother] I think that's exactly
what they acknowledged you for.
[brother] Then is that place
a specialized school for music?
What's up with us both
going together?
[slams table]
[Tomori] That day,
we saw my mother
grovel on the ground and beg
for the first time
in our lives.
My mother, who raised us
for the longest time,
all by herself.
It looked like
a fairly normal school,
and I immediately made
a few friends.
However, every day
after classes were over,
I was forced to take something
like a physical exam.
We were supposedly
in the same school,
but I couldn't see
my brother at all.
Every time I tried to go
and look for him,
my friends would always
stop me from doing so.
What I didn't know was
that my brother
had been turned
into an experimental subject.
My brother's special ability
was to make air vibrate
to his will.
He used that ability
during a live performance
to change the sound
of his guitar in unusual ways.
That's how they found him.
Scientists believed
that my brother's ability
could be harnessed
to disrupt communications
or even jack the airwaves
if focused correctly.
A year later, I was finally
allowed to see my brother,
but he was no longer
the big brother I remembered.
He couldn't even recognize
that I was his little sister.
His memories were gone.
The classmates that had been
keeping me away from my brother
were placed around me
by the scientists
to pretend to be my friends.
The reason they were
examining me every day
was because, if one sibling
has an ability,
chances are that
the other one will, too.
And that was the only reason.
I swore that I wouldn't trust
anyone ever again.
I snuck out of that school.
What happened
after you left there?
I met the one person
I could truly trust,
and that's how I'm here now.
‐[Yu] That person is...?
‐Oh. We're getting off here.
I'm Nao Tomori.
I'm here to see my brother.
[Yu] So her first name is "Nao."
[receptionist] He's in room 12.
Go ahead.
Think it would be OK
if I took him outside?
[receptionist] As long as you
keep to our grounds, no problem.
[Tomori] Thank you so much.
This way.
He's here.
Hmm?
[gasp]
[brother screaming]
Guess the painkillers
have worn off again.
Your brother.
What in the world
is he doing?
[Tomori] He's composing.
My brother thinks that he's
actually playing a guitar.
All of those grunts
and groans you hear
is him singing the main melody.
[brother groaning]
[nurse] Oh!
[Tomori thinking] Oh, man.
He ruined another comforter.
Would you like to go outside?
It's the time of day when you
see the best scenery.
It's amazing.
[Tomori] Isn't it, though?
Yeah.
But an environment this special,
how in the world did you
pull it off?
It's all thanks
to the one person I can trust.
He transferred my brother
to the hospital
in this beautiful place
free of charge.
[Yu] There's actually someone
out there that generous?
[sighs]
He shows no interest at all.
But maybe someday someone will
come up with a miracle drug
that can cure this.
Nobody is doing research on how
to save patients like this.
Well, why not?
For the scientists,
people that have abilities
are just like batteries.
If one runs out of power,
they can just experiment
with another.
There's no incentive for them
to help the test subjects
that end up like this.
I'm stunned.
We don't know whether or not
something will happen to us
tomorrow, either.
Now you're just talking crazy.
[Tomori] How about you choose
your words carefully?
‐[Yu] Sorry.
‐[Tomori] Well then,
let's go back.
You're really having a hard time
with all this, aren't you?
[Tomori]
You're sympathizing?
Well, stop that.
You're nothing but
a dishonest cheater.
[Yu] She's right.
This is unlike me.
‐I'm home.
‐[Ayumi groans]
I didn't think the student
council would be something
that keeps me this busy.
‐Nothing I can do about it.
‐Huh?
Big Brother, you're
part of the student council?
‐You mean I didn't tell you?
‐This is the first
I'm hearing it!
In that case, you need
to eat some of my special
rolling vegetable curry
to renew your energy.
[Yu] If I have
a special ability,
there is the possibility
that Ayumi will have one, too.
If I were to be captured,
Ayumi could end up
just like Tomori.
[Ayumi] It's done!
‐It looks great.
‐I hope you really like it.
So sweet!
Uh, well, um, can it be
that the secret ingredient
of this curry is...
Pizza sauce: the secret
ingredient of our household!
[Yu] Oh, man, this tastes
no different
from all the omelet rice
she's made.
[Ayumi gasping] Wow!
I guess it's your daily routine,
but hurry up and go to sleep.
I was able to see a comet today,
so I'm deeply moved
and can go to sleep
totally excited!
That's pretty skillful of you.
[Ayumi] But the comet
that I really want to see
is a completely different one.
‐Oh?
‐A comet with
a really long orbit!
‐[Yu] What is that?
‐It's a comet that swings
by us only once
every few centuries!
They have comets like that, huh?
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]