So what is it you do
on your days off?
How about some tea
later today?
‐And it's really cute.
‐Yusarin, you should go too!
‐Sure, that sounds good to me.
Aww, come on, how long are
they gonna keep this up?
Can you blame them?
Yusarin is a pop idol.
This was bound to happen soon.
[Yu] Huh? What's going on?
I think I might know, but it's
probably better if you don't.
‐Huh?
‐[desk rattles]
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
First, for Rika!
Next, for Yuriko!
[Yu thinking] Group beating?
Not cool.
Though I guess it's expected
when she does stuff like that
without thinking.
[Tomori] Oww!
So, uh, are you all right?
You were watching
the whole time.
You tell me.
[electronic ringtone plays]
[Tomori] Oh. Our comrade
is going to appear.
‐[door opens]
‐Huh? [gasp]
Oh, my gosh,
what happened to you?
‐I just got beaten by a mob.
‐[Yusa whimpers]
[Yusa] Are you all right?
Shouldn't you go to a hospital?
[Tomori] I'm used to it,
I'll be fine.
So, who are we
going to pummel?
I'm not going.
Too much of a hassle.
You're so boring.
[bang!]
The ability is...
floating on air.
All right, we got this!
Check it out!
[Yu] A flying humanoid is found
in Japan as well?
Are they saying that this
black shadow is that person?
[Tomori] For the moment,
it's only a scoop
in a small occult magazine.
But if we leave this alone,
it will turn into a huge deal.
‐Let's go.
‐[Yu] Where to?
[Takajo] Here,
in the middle of the mountains.
This is just a hunch, but I
think that's where our target
is practicing how to fly.
If we stake out that location,
they're bound to appear
at some point.
[Yu] Just how long of a stakeout
are you thinking?
‐No clue. Until they show up.
‐[bleep]
[Takajo] Don't make Yusarin
say something like that!
We could be in for a long haul,
so we should probably stock up
at the supermarket first.
‐Seriously?
‐Um, can you go back
to being sweet Yusa, please?
I don't like your tone,
four‐eyes.
Give me one good reason why I
should take orders from you!
'Cause you always end up
like this.
Some team we've got.
Just my luck.
All right, you guys,
let's get going.
[Tomori humming]
So is there a reason you're
getting so much corn?
Because you can't
have a barbecue without
roasted corn.
Barbecue? If you do that,
they'll know that we're all
out there.
True, but who's to say
this person won't decide
to approach us on their own?
Huh? Yeah, like that'll happen.
[Tomori] What else?
Steak meat, spare ribs,
sausages.
OK, so now you're thinking
only about meat.
‐Yeah, because meat is good.
‐Watch and learn.
Oh, shishito?
The spice gives
a nice accent to flavors.
Fine, we'll get them,
but they better not touch
my meat, OK?
Those two have been getting
along rather well lately,
haven't they?
Hey, do you think
they could be dating?
[Takajo] It hasn't been long
since they first met,
so I don't think it's gone
that far.
But they are a couple
that's pleasant to watch.
Yeah. I think they're
well‐suited for each other.
All alone with Yusarin!
I'm so glad I'm alive!
All right, boys, you two
get to carry the tent
and the barbecue grill.
Kurobane and I will carry
all the food to the campsite.
Tent? You mean we're
spending the night?
I told you, we're going to stay
on stakeout until our target
shows up.
Excuse me. I didn't bring
a change of clothes, so, um...
You won't die if you wear
the same thing.
Now let's go.
All right, we're here.
We should set up the tents
before dark.
‐Right.
‐Huh?
Careful.
It's dangerous over there.
Huh? Whoa!
[Yu] What is this?
‐The remnants of a well.
‐[Yu] Why didn't you say
anything about it earlier?
Well, if you fell, that would
have been funny in a way.
Don't make jokes about
life‐or‐death situations.
‐Why don't we set it up
further that way?
‐[Takajo] Good call.
[Tomori] Don't worry. I'll plug
up the big hole just as soon
as we're done setting up.
[Yu] Sorry, there's
a student council camp,
so I don't think
I'll make it home tonight.
[Ayumi] You can't come home?
It's awfully sudden.
That's right.
That's why I'm sorry.
‐[Ayumi coughs]
‐Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine.
No worries.
‐Later.
‐Roger that.
‐This could be useful.
‐Don't use me as a lighter.
I am not a camping kit.
[Yu]
What are you thinking?
This makes us stand out
way too much.
Mmm! Roasted corn
is so delicious!
OK, come on, everyone, eat up.
Hmm. I guess she can have this.
[Yusa] Huh? What just...?
Here, have some roasted corn,
Yusa!
Thank you so much!
Oh, my! Tasty!
I know, right?
When it comes to roasted corn,
I'm your girl.
We'll have meat soon!
Mmm. Eat vegetables, too.
Spare ribs are so good!
The wieners are super juicy
when you crunch into them!
Don't have just meat.
Sandwich some vegetables
in the middle when you eat.
‐Oh! This meat is so delicious.
‐This sauce is the best!
And in the end, I'm the only one
eating any vegetables.
So you only eat meat, too,
just like my big sister.
[Yu] Oh, is that so?
Yes, she was
a very finicky eater.
She was?
Hey, I'd be interested to know
what kind of person
your big sister was to you.
Well, let's see.
Big sister and I have basically
polar opposite personalities.
She was such a tomboy that
no boy in the neighborhood
could win against her.
But to me, she was
a very kind big sister.
And I loved her
exactly the way she was.
No matter what, I always
tagged along behind her.
Oh! Sorry, I'm talking too much.
When it comes to my sister,
I get so carried away.
No. I kind of understand
how you feel, actually.
[owl hoots]
‐[roar on video game]
‐[Yusarin screams]
There are way too many enemies.
I think I'm
in really big trouble.
Don't you worry, leave
everything to the mighty Taka‐‐
I don't need your stupid help!
Arrrgggh!
[Takajo] That was my moment
to shine!
[Yu] You guys are
completely forgetting
the reason why we're here.
Hold on... where?
‐[music on earphones]
‐Is there something wrong?
Well, um... no, nothing.
So, uh, what is that music?
You listen to it
day in and day out.
This? It's a band
called Zhiend.
Never heard of them.
‐[Tomori] My brother loved them.
‐Huh?
Are you sure you're OK?
Yeah.
Mind if I listen to that
for a bit?
[guitar ballad plays]
[woman]
♪ Looking up high... ♪
[Yu] Why...
I think I've felt this before.
[Tomori] How is it?
♪ Wondering how
I would feel... ♪
It's kind of strange.
I feel like I'm standing
all alone in a vast, open space.
Ha‐ha! You understand it,
don't you?
You are so on point.
The music Zhiend creates
is incredibly vast
and downlight lonely‐feeling.
I believe it's because
the vocalist, who also
composes the songs,
is completely blind.
Her words paint scenery
extending as far as you can go.
For now, I'm only recording
this poor, misguided cheater,
but my dream is to film
a Zhiend music video.
[Yu] She's never had
this expression before.
[Tomori] Of course, filming
a documentary would be OK, too.
[Yu] Yeah.
Don’t film poor old me.
Just go ahead and film them
if you want.
[Tomori]
Don’t worry, I'm never gonna
film you again, I promise.
[humming with song]
Keep it. I'm giving it to you.
Huh? No way.
I'd feel bad about it.
I have quite a bit saved up
thanks to a few of our jobs.
I can just buy a new one,
so don't worry about it.
[Yu] I see.
Then I'll take it.
[Tomori] Good.
Two will keep watch at a time.
We'll take shifts
all the way until morning.
The boys will sleep four hours,
then switch places with us.
[owl hoots]
[soft guitar music plays]
[Takajo] Hey, Otosaka.
It's our turn now.
[Yu sighs]
Hey, time to switch.
[Yu, groggily] Oh,
it's that time already?
[Yu] This again.
Who was that person?
Whoa! A trout!
I caught a rainbow trout!
Damn it.
I'll catch one bigger than that.
Trout, trout, come to me now!
I'm not going to lose either.
‐[splash]
‐All right, got one!
[Tomori] Oh, wow,
rainbow trout is tasty.
[Takajo] Yusarin, this one
is cooked perfectly.
I'm not Yusarin!
But I guess
I'll let her enjoy it.
[Yusa] Huh?
Oh. Are you sure you don't want
to eat it, Takajo?
I'm sure. It's all yours.
Ahhh!
[Yusa] Oh, it's so delicious!
‐Things like this are nice
every so often.
‐[Yusa] Yes!
[Yu] Is it me,
or does she just want to play?
So, um, are we spending
the night again?
Yes. Is there a problem
with that?
I was thinking I'd like
to take a bath today.
[Tomori] That's fine.
I have one all ready.
‐Come on, I'll show you.
‐[Yusa] Huh?
‐Uh... how nice.
‐Here's a towel and some soap.
[Misa] You've got some nerve.
You set this up and just assumed
I would jump right in.
I'll keep an eye out
in case the boys decide
to try peeping. OK?
[Yu] You said there was
a bath all ready?
‐It's only for girls.
‐[Yu] Huh?
You boys can clean yourselves
down at the river.
I can't bathe in the water
that Yusarin has bathed in?!
Turnoff!
[Yu] You don't look that ripped
when you have clothes on.
[Takajo] Because of my ability,
I had to train my body.
Regardless of how much armor
I would wear under my uniform,
I had to build a body
that wouldn’t get too injured
when I teleported.
You did all that just so you
could properly use your ability?
Yes. But I doubt that I'll be
the only one who does that.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
[Takajo] In the future,
you may face a challenge
that's beyond your expectations
and that forces you
to make a change.
‐You never know.
‐[chuckles] Yeah.
Because taking someone over
for only five seconds
is so useful.
It's because you haven't...
Just forget I said anything.
What? Come on, now.
You got me curious.
With an attractive face
like that,
you might have some issues
dealing with the ladies.
Of course, just saying that
gets under my skin.
You're telling me.
I was just dumped
by an intelligent
and beautiful girl
thanks to this ability.
A wise choice.
I think we should focus
on love and romance
only after we are freed
of these abilities.
[Yu] How old do we need to be
for them to be gone?
[Takajo] It should happen
by the time we graduate
high school.
Two more years.
That's a long time.
[Takajo] Yes. For us,
it is a very long time.
You know what?
This is way too cold.
[sneezes]
[Misa sighs]
Ah, this feels good.
[Tomori] We'll sleep using
the same rotation as yesterday.
[Yu] Tomorrow is Monday, right?
Are we gonna go to school
from here?
Haven't you been listening?
We're staking out
until they show up.
This is ridiculous.
It feels like we're all trying
to live out here or something.
[Tomori] That's exactly
what I'm after.
Besides, it's not like
ditching class will affect
our school reports at all.
Even so, I'd like to go home
at some point.
I have a younger sister.
Yes, I already know that.
Then I'll promise to be
back in the morning.
Just let me go home.
[Tomori] I can't. If I allow
that for you, everyone else
will say the same thing.
‐[Tomori] Besides, I think
it'll be all right.
‐[Yu] What will?
I'm sure everything will be
squared away by tomorrow.
Man, I'm really sick of corn.
[boy] Excuse me.
What do you guys think you're
doing all the way out here?
Someone really showed up.
Is this the guy?
Well, we all met after
running away from our homes.
We hit it off pretty well
so we decided to set up camp
together.
[Yu]
Another obvious lie.
I take it, since you're camping,
that you intend to stay here.
Yes. We’re planning
to stay here forever.
It's not like people
will find us here.
[Saito] Really?
Well, I found you.
And I'm sure your parents
are worried as well.
If you're thinking of calling
the police, you should know
that they'll arrest you, too.
‐What for?
‐Simple. It's private property.
[others gasp]
And then there's this.
That’s you, isn't it?
What is that, a magazine?
[Tomori] A scoop article on you
practicing flight.
You're joking.
It's too easy to get caught
if you practiced
in public mountains.
But this place is private
and conveniently close
to the boundary of Tokyo.
Normally, you'd be fine,
but we camped out
and showed no sign of leaving.
You got restless and decided
to try and scare us off.
Once we were gone, you could
practice flying again in peace.
If you really believe that,
you must be insane.
I'll call the police for you.
[Tomori] You're not very sane
either if you're coming out here
all by yourself.
I came to pick some chestnuts.
[Tomori] There aren't any
chestnuts this time of year.
And you can't deny
that you were out here
because I already captured you
on film.
How very sad for you.
You little brat!
Give it to me now!
‐Yes!
‐You used the well to trap him?
‐[whoosh!]
Of course.
If you fall into a hole that
you don't know the bottom of,
you use your ability.
I put some hay at the bottom,
just in case I was wrong.
But thanks to you, I have some
amazing footage for a scoop.
She set a trap out here and
didn't even tell us about it?
She is just like the devil.
Give me the camera!
[Tomori shrieks]
Otosaka, take over his body!
Then I'll defeat him using
my teleport ability.
No way.
That hurts every time I do it.
‐[Saito] Hyah!
‐Damn it!
Thanks a lot.
‐He's escaping.
‐And so fast.
[Yu] I have no choice.
[wind whistling]
[gasp]
I'm so high up!
[Yusa whimpers]
I have to control it for now.
Stop... stop... stop!
Stop!
‐[gasp]
‐You took such
a reckless risk there.
I should have just
taken him over immediately
instead of complaining.
Oww! What is this?
What just happened?
Well, a bruise
or a broken bone for one.
You're pretty lucky.
My camcorder is fine, too.
It's a good thing you survived.
[Saito] What the hell?
Who are you guys?
We all have special abilities
like you.
But these abilities are kind of
like diseases that only show up
during adolescence.
They'll disappear, but if
someone finds out about you,
you'll turn into a guinea pig
for scientists.
You don't want that, do you?
And what would happen
if your ability disappeared
while you were flying?
You would fall to your death.
Is this something
to risk your life over?
Misa, if you would, please.
Of course.
I see.
I thought that this power to fly
was something granted
just to me.
But I guess
there are others, too.
What a bummer.
I wanted to fry freely someday.
I even had a dream of becoming
"Sky‐high Saito,"
the biggest star in Hollywood.
[Yu]
What a corny name?!
I understand the feeling,
but for the sake
of your life and future,
please don't use
your ability anymore.
I got it.
[Tomori] Thank you so much.
‐That ended peacefully.
‐Phew! That took so long.
Yeah. That's totally
how I feel.
I'm back.
[groans]
I didn't think
the student council was
something this busy.
I can't help it.
[Ayumi] I know you're
very competent,
but are you being pulled
all over the place?
It's really nothing
that extravagant.
Well then, in honor
of my big brother
and all of his hard work,
I have prepared a feast!
Chanpon noodles
with lots of vegetables!
[Yu] It's not red.
This is... doable!
‐It's time to dig in.
‐It's time to eat.
[Yu] At last!
So, how is it?
[Yu] Delicious!
So delicious it makes me cry!
[Ayumi] Actually, I wanted
to use the pizza sauce
as a secret ingredient,
but I only have
a tiny bit left.
If you can make food that's this
delicious without pizza sauce,
can't you leave it out
of all the other food, too?
The Otosaka pizza sauce
secret recipe
needs to be handed down
to the last generation.
But when I was about to go
to the supermarket,
the security guard stopped me.
I couldn't buy
the ingredients for it.
[Yu] Nice security!
This is the first thing
that's made me feel happy
about moving here.
But this is delicious
all on its own,
so you really don't need
any secret ingredients.
If you say so.
That saves me a lot.
[Yu] Yes.
I succeeded in getting rid
of that pizza sauce
‐once and for all!
‐[Ayumi coughs]
You really aren't feeling well,
are you?
[Ayumi] No, no.
I'm totally fine now.
By the way,
I had so many stories
that I wanted you to hear
while you were gone,
Big Brother.
Yeah? What stories?
For starters, I was suddenly
asked out
by one of the boys
in my class the other day.
‐What? And what did you do?
‐Oh, you know.
Oh, don't give me that.
[giggles] I politely declined
the offer.
Oh, man, that could have been
a pivotal moment
that would have changed
your entire life.
[Ayumi] Aww. What do you mean,
Big Brother?
‐Do you want me to have
a boyfriend or something?
‐It depends on the guy.
[Ayumi] It's gonna have to be
someone better
than my big brother.
‐[Yu] Hmm. Someone like that
is a rarity.
‐[Ayumi] You're right.
‐[coughs]
‐Oh, I'm sorry.
You might have
a cold or something.
A fever.
How is your appetite?
It's OK. I can finish eating
all of this, no problem.
[Yu] 37.8°.
You totally have a cold.
After your body is warmed up
from your bath,
you need to crawl
right into your bed.
Right. Roger that.
[coughs]
I'm sorry.
Can you fall asleep like this?
I'll be all right.
Don't you worry.
OK. Sleep tight, Ayumi.
Good night.
Good night. Sweet dreams.
[Yu] Well, if she stays put,
she should be all right.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]