[monitor beeping]
[Yu gasps]
[shrieking]
It... hurts.
[Shichino] Of course it hurts.
It's only been two days
since the surgery.
‐[Yu] Two days?
‐[Shichino] That’s right.
[Yu] Why can't I move?
[Shichino] Like I know.
Ask the doctor.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
Hey, are you feeling
any better?
[Yu] Medoki?
[Medoki] I'm glad.
Just like we planned.
We were able
to prevent a collapse.
[Shichino]
We didn't plan anything.
We're just dealing with it.
[Medoki] If that was the case,
you would have done more
than just give him a shot.
[Shichino] I'm not a doctor.
[Yu] Um, what happened to me?
How did I end up here
like this?
[gasp] Tomori.
Is Tomori all right?
[Maedomari] She's fine.
She's also here
in this hospital.
Yeah, thanks to Kumagami.
[Yu] I see.
I'm glad.
And how is he doing?
Huh? It can't be.
‐[Medoki] Yes.
‐[gasp]
It wouldn't have happened if you
weren't so damn busy trying
to save your own ass.
You have no room to complain.
You were the one who said
we should bet everything
‐on his ability to time‐leap,
did you forget that?
‐No way... Kumagami is...
Those guys must have decided
that they didn't need
your time leap
to get what they wanted.
Collapse was the biggest threat
to them
so they tried to use
hostages as shields.
Both sides miscalculated.
It's all my fault.
You shouldn't blame yourself.
‐[Yu] Hey.
‐[Medoki] Hmm?
[Yu] Are we gonna have to deal
with this stuff all the time?
[Medoki] Not from those two,
at least.
We erased their memories using
Maedomari's ability.
But there's no telling when you
might be targeted next.
All in all, I'm just glad
you woke up.
We’ve been taking turns
watching you.
Hey, uh, it's time now.
Right.
‐Hold on.
I have one more question.
‐What is it?
Why isn't my brother here?
‐Really? Are you that stupid?!
‐No, you need to calm down.
‐What does he mean?
‐[Shichino] Let go!
He means that,
for your big brother,
Kumagami was his best friend
in the world.
[wind whistles]
‐[knock on door]
‐Yes, come in.
‐Hey, Big Brother.
‐[Yu] Oh, Ayumi.
It's been a while.
Are you sure it's OK to talk?
Yeah.
As long as I stay still.
They said you'll never see
from your right eye again.
Apparently, it was such
a big accident,
I shouldn’t be alive.
I'd rather lose one eye
than my life.
‐[Ayumi] But...
‐With proper rehabilitation,
they said I could live a life
that's almost the same
as before.
It would be nice
if that's the case.
How are things at the facility?
Everyone is super nice to me
so it's been really great.
But Big Brother Shun
has looked heartbroken
since the accident happened.
I'm worried about him.
[Yu thinking] Big brother.
Losing Ayumi was the most
painful thing that's
happened to me.
For Shunsuke, Kumagami was
someone just as special.
And if I had died
because of the collapse,
what would Ayumi
have gone through?
‐[knock on door]
‐Yes, come in.
Hey there, it's been a while.
[Yu] Takajo, it really does feel
like it's been a while.
You look like you're in
a lot more pain
than I had imagined.
Yeah. What a sight, huh?
And I come bearing gifts.
I think this will make you
perk right up.
What is all this?
A lunch box with insulation!
And the contents are...
[drumroll plays]
The smell. I know it.
‐[fanfare plays]
‐[Takajo] That's right!
‐[Takajo] The cafeteria's
beef tongue curry!
Whoa! I never thought I'd
have it in this place.
‐I can even help you eat it.
‐Please do.
‐[Takajo] Say ahh!
‐[Yu] Ahh!
So good! This reminds me
of the days back in school.
Yes, this is truly the taste
of our adolescence.
‐Another bite, please! Ahh!
‐There's still plenty left,
so just eat until
you get bored of it.
By the way,
how is Tomori doing?
Her injuries are a lot less
severe than yours,
‐so they'll probably
let her out soon.
‐That's good to hear.
[Takajo] You've had
a lot of hardships lately.
No kidding.
We're looking forward
to you guys
coming back to the council
once you’ve healed up.
Granted, I love holding down
the fort with Yusarin,
but it's just not the same.
‐[knock on door]
‐[Yu] Yes? Come in.
I came to visit!
Uh... aah!
Hey, Kurobane.
What’s up?
Not much. I made this for you
if you're interested.
Ah, would that be cream stew,
by any chance?
That's amazing, you got it!
Yusarin's handmade
cream stew!
This recipe is cherished
in the Kurobane household
as a tasty source
of strength.
It even works wonders
on illnesses and injuries.
[Yu] I see.
So that's the reason
she brought me cream stew
that day.
Thanks a lot.
Yep. Now then, open wide.
Uh... ahh!
Ahh... up!
Well? What do you think?
Mmm. Great. I feel a bit more
energetic already.
Ahh? I'm so glad.
[Yu] Takajo can never know
this happened.
[Yu] Misa, you there?
Hmm? Huh?
[whoosh!]
[Misa] Calling on the dead now?
Yeah. Where do people go
when they die?
Who knows?
I never left this place.
I'm like a candle that Yusa
is holding onto.
When her ability fades away,
my flame gets
snuffed out with it,
just like a candle in the wind.
I see. In that case,
shouldn't you use
all the time you have
to visit your loved ones?
Huh? What's all this about?
I almost died the other day
and it made me think.
You could be gone at any point
in time, you know.
You should visit your friends
while you still can.
I hear ya.
I know I got one more chance,
but that doesn't make it
any easier.
You know, I used
to eat that a lot.
It used to be
our mom's best dish.
But Yusa copied her and made it
all the freakin' time.
[Yu] Just like our family.
Unlike Yusa, I made
our parents miserable,
though you could say dying
was the worst way
to be a bad daughter.
[Yu] Then you should go
see them again, before
the ability is gone.
Yeah. Well, I'll take that
suggestion into consideration.
[whoosh!]
‐[Yusa] Was I asleep again?!
‐No, you're all right.
If you don't mind me asking,
Yusa, what do your parents
do for a living?
Oh, yes, they make soba noodles
deep in the mountains of Nagano
and serve them.
I see. Then I suggest you go
visit them sometime soon.
‐Huh?
‐[Yu] No, you don't have
any time left, go now!
S‐Sure. I'll talk it out
with my manager right away.
[Yu] This is really gonna take
some getting used to.
Fairly close to Last Supper,
"Fair Supper" for short.
This is a show
where celebrities...
She made regular appearances
on a show like this?
[Yusa] ... wouldn't be their
last supper but is a supper
fairly close to it.
On today's show,
I'll be introducing you
to the Fair Supper from me,
Yusarin!
It's just over this hill.
[announcer] Actually,
this is a soba restaurant...
[Yu] She used her work to go see
her parents, huh?
Nice Yusa.
[announcer] ... and she seems
very happy about it.
[Yusa, giggling] Hi!
[Yusa] This is the handmade soba
and wild greens
tempura set‐meal.
First, I'll have some
of the tasty soba.
I'll take the dipping sauce
and dunk it.
Mmm‐mm.
So good!
Next up, I'll have
some mugwort tempura.
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
This is really tasty too!
[giggles]
[Yu] With such
a lack of vocabulary,
I'm surprised they chose you
to be the host of a food show.
[Misa] Honestly,
there's nothing special
about the taste.
It's so plain, in fact,
you could get the same
from a store.
Misa! What the heck
are you doing?
But the love of my parents
is the secret ingredient
that makes this so exquisite.
That's why I love this dish.
Nothing can ever replace it.
Thanks for the awesome meal.
[mother] You reminded me
of Misa just now.
‐[mother] I'm sorry.
‐[father] Yeah.
She was a delinquent with
a bad mouth and attitude,
but she was good deep down.
That was a great way
to repay them.
‐[knock on door]
‐Uh, yes? Come in.
Good morning, brother!
Oh, hey, good morning.
Ta‐da!
Happy birthday
to the best brother ever!
‐Huh?
‐Today is your 16th birthday!
Congrats on another trip
around the sun!
No kidding, it is?
I would never forget
such an important day.
So I made sure to pull out
all the stops.
[lighthearted music plays]
Uh... what's wrong?
Don’t you want to eat it?
[Yu] Yeah, of course.
Yeah! Then open wide
for the airplane.
I can eat it by myself.
That's silly. You're recovering,
so take it easy.
Ahhh!
[Yu] Huh?
It's sweet but it's good.
[Ayumi] Here.
[Yu]
It's the same flavor.
Maybe it's that ingredient
Misa was talking about.
So, do you like it?
‐It's great.
‐I'm so happy!
‐[Ayumi] Now next. Next, next!
‐[Yu] Tasty.
[Yu] Guess my vocab's limited,
too.
I probably shouldn't
criticize Yusa.
[clapping]
‐Grats on getting all better.
‐I'm coming along, anyway.
There's a favor I'd like
to ask of you.
[Yu] Hey, bro.
I heard you'd been
up here all along.
Could you please say something?
[Shunsake] This hospital's
all right.
You won't have to deal
with the police here.
[Yu] More than that.
I...
[Yu] He's just like
how I was back then.
The terrorists are acting up
overseas.
Japan will become involved
shortly.
‐[Yu] Huh?
‐[Shunsake] And Kumagami is
no longer here either.
I wonder, what will happen
to all of us?
It's been a while.
Uh‐huh. Uh, Tomori!
Oh, gee,
it's nice to see you, too.
W‐Well, I was just surprised.
The hospital discharged me
a little while ago.
So I thought I'd come
and have a chat with you.
Have you heard anything
from your big brother yet?
[Yu] He said Japan will soon
be involved
in the activates
of overseas terrorists.
[Tomori] Interesting.
My brother's had all the life
knocked out of him.
He's so different.
Dangerous people may keep coming
after me in the future.
I don't want to lose anyone
or make them miserable
ever again.
If there's something I could do
with my powers,
I'd like to do it,
but I don't know how.
Tomori, what am I
supposed to do?
[Tomori] There's only one thing
I can think of.
All right, what is it?
Please, tell me.
Your big brother's
research facility.
The scientists there
have already completed
the anti‐ability vaccine
in preparation for Charlotte.
Yeah?
So then, everything ends
if you can plunder
all of the abilities
that exist,
as well as any new ones
that might happen to sprout up
in the meantime.
Of course there are risks.
What will happen to you
after gaining
thousands upon thousands
of abilities?
[Yu] What will happen?
[Tomori] You might turn
into a monster
that can potentially annihilate
the human race.
Even then, will you be able
to hold on to your sanity?
It definitely won't be easy.
But it's something
only you can do.
That is the only method
I can think of
that can save all
of the ability wielders.
To be honest, I wasn't planning
on having this talk with you.
But... you came back here
from the future
in order to save Ayumi.
Then you came to rescue me
and Kumagami too.
At first, I thought you were
just a filthy cheater,
but I can believe
in the person you've become.
That's a drastic change
of opinion.
Well, this is way too
reckless for it to be
one of my tactics.
Forget I mentioned it.
Now, you should probably
be getting some rest.
Later.
‐[Yu] Hold on.
‐Hmm?
I'll try it.
[Tomori] No way, it's reckless.
I'm serious.
Besides, I kind of owe you one.
And if you think it's
the only way, that's all I need.
Your motive is a bit weak.
But what happened to us could
very well happen again.
This time I'll be
the one that saves you.
‐I promise.
‐Why is that?
Because I love you.
Huh? What are you talking about?
You mean like romance?
Yeah, romance.
You say that
with such a straight face.
I don't think there was ever
a time that you thought
favorably of me.
I've said this before,
but in a different world
I threw myself into despair,
and you were there
the whole time
watching over me.
[Tomori] This is just
a wild guess,
but wasn't that my way
of taking responsibility
for Ayumi's death?
Yes, but you still
saved me.
So, how do you stumble
from that
into a full‐blown romance?
It doesn't make
any sense at all.
Right, like you need reasoning
to fall in love.
You're the one who's using it
as a reason, you big moron!
[both growling]
[Tomori] See? Our compatibility
is absolutely the worst.
[Yu] But I still love you.
You’re so strange,
you know that?
‐Say whatever you like.
‐[sigh]
OK, fine, I'll say it.
I'll be waiting, here.
Huh? For what?
For when you've saved
the ability wielders
and finally come back
to me.
Once you've pulled that off,
the two of us can become lovers.
Aren't you overestimating
my abilities?
Think of it as incentive.
If you really manage
to do this,
I've no doubt you will be
irresistibly dear to me,
after such a big feat.
[Yu] That sounds
like a challenge.
So, has that increased
your motivation?
[Yu] Yeah, bigtime.
Then promise me.
Swear you'll come back.
We will meet again.
I know it.
Yeah.
I'll make sure to come back.
If you lie, you'll cut off
the tip of your finger.
Pinkie promise!
That's a scary promise.
So that you'll keep
your motivation up.
Sure.
Good. Then start with me.
You're going to plunder
every single ability, remember?
I see. This is what
the mission entails.
Hadn't thought of that.
‐Yep, go ahead.
‐[Yu] I'm sorry.
There's really no need
to apologize.
I'll finally be
a regular human again.
Thank you very much.
[Yu] Big brother,
I have a plan.
I'm going to go plunder
the abilities of every
wielder in the world
and save them.
[Shunsake] That's impossible.
Don’t bother.
Out of all
the ability wielders,
I'm the strongest,
aren't I?
I don't want Kumagami's
sacrifice to have been a waste!
You're not the only one
who feels that way!
Damn it. Damn it!
He saved me so many ways
just by being at my side.
But I didn’t even get to say
thanks to him in the end.
[Yu] That's why I'm going.
So that no one
who's important to me
will ever suffer again.
Don't you feel that way, too,
especially after losing
Kumagami?
Are you serious about this?
Sure am. I've already taken
Tomori's ability.
Taken...?
The wheels are already
in motion.
and I'm not turning back.
[Shichino]
That's some determination.
But how are you going to search
for ability wielders?
Someone close
to the syndicate's leader
must have an ability similar
to what Kumagami had.
They couldn't gather
that many ability wielders
in such a short time otherwise.
Yu, fly overseas.
Leave Japan to the rest of us.
We lost Kumagami.
But we're still a powerful
syndicate in our own right.
We'll hold them down until
their abilities are gone.
If we can't do that much,
we couldn't possibly look him
in the eye again.
Yu, you just turned 16,
isn't that right?
‐[Yu] Yeah.
‐You don't have much time left.
You'll have to do all this
in record time.
Right.
[Takajo] Otosaka.
[Yu] Oh, hey, guys.
I heard the whole story
from Tomori.
[Misa] We want you to take
our powers too.
If it helps you even
just a little bit,
it'll be worth it.
Take Yusa's too.
Misa, you know
what that means for you?
Yeah, I'm cool with it.
This is as good a spot
as any for me to fade.
Come on, dude.
Don’t make this harder
than it has to be.
[Takajo] That's right, Otosaka.
Go ahead.
All right then.
If you're absolutely
sure about this.
Yeah. See ya.
Right.
[energy pulses]
[Yusa, gasping] What the...?
Sorry, did I doze off again?
Yusa, your big sister entrusted
me with this letter to you.
[opening letter]
"Yusa, I've had
a blast lately.
It was fun hanging out
with those guys
from the student council.
I felt that I wanted to be
with you forever.
[Misa] But the one thing that
was hardest for me, Yusa,
was that I was always
right there with you,
yet we never really saw
each other.
I love you more than anything.
And now I'll be a good
dead person and fade out.
Goodbye for now.
From Misa."
[Yusa, sobbing] My big sister
was always together
with all of you,
wasn't she?
‐Yeah. We had
a lot of fun together.
‐Indeed.
In that case, I'm glad.
‐Otosaka, don't keep us waiting
too long, OK?
‐Yeah.
After all,
we're high‐school buddies
who suffered together.
We're friends for life.
We'll be waiting here for you.
So get back to us
as soon as you can.
‐[Yu] Right.
‐[Yusa] Yep.
[woman singing in Japanese]
About frickin' time.
Take this, I insist.
It isn't much, but it's
all I can do for now.
What is it?
While you're there,
it should help you get by,
if only a little bit.
[Yu] You made this
in one night?
I know what your standardized
test scores are like.
Yeah. After all, I'm just
a filthy cheater, aren't I?
Fine. In return, I want you
to hold onto this for me.
Sure, I understand.
It'll be here
when you get back.
[Yu] I'm uneasy.
It's all so uncertain.
But I have to do this,
because I am
the only one that can.
Well, it's time to go.
Right, have a safe trip, 'K?