Hey, Yu, Ayumi.
It's been a while.
[phone ringing]
What is it?
‐Um... Who are you again?
‐He's our big brother.
I had to erase
the memories you had of me.
I didn't want to,
but it was necessary.
Necessary?
I don't understand.
Well, there was
a lot going on.
Seems like it, big bro.
Uh... huh?
Yu, it seems that
you're finally fully aware
of the true ability
that you wield.
That's why I had you
come here together.
I would have ended up here
whether you brought us or not.
‐Convenient.
‐What do you mean by that?
It's a long story.
[Shunsake]
So you used my time leap.
Well, that was
a job well done.
[Yu] What's gonna happen now?
Can you maybe come home
and live with us?
More like the reverse.
You can plunder
any ability that you want.
You were the strongest
of all ability wielders.
You even have the power
of time leap.
That makes you a liability.
What are you trying to say?
There are syndicates around that
would try to use your powers.
I can't let you live
in the open anymore.
You'll have to remain here
until your powers fade.
‐For real?
‐[Shunsake] Yeah.
[Shunsake] You may already know,
but we created this research
facility as a safehouse
for ability wielders.
In other words, this is the best
place that you could be.
Come with me.
Hmm? Look who it is.
So nice of you to drop by.
Grandpa here
is head of the research team.
‐Dr. Tsutsumiuchi.
‐[Yu] I know.
[Yu] He's the one
that saved me back then.
And this?
A research facility that
is creating a vaccine
to prevent future outbreaks
of special abilities.
Vaccine?
You mean we're all sick?
Yes. The special abilities
are a disease.
So before particles are spread
all over Earth again,
we need to vaccinate
every person in the world.
[Yu] Particles?
Have you ever heard
of a long‐orbit comet
by the name of Charlotte?
Yes! I know about it, sir.
Oh, you must really like
the stars a lot, young lady.
‐That's right. Stargazing
is my favorite hobby.
‐Mm‐hmm.
Charlotte's long orbit
brings it by Earth
every 75 years.
And when it does,
an unknown particle
is showered
onto our planet's surface.
Those who inhale the particles
generate special powers
during the times
when they are most sensitive.
The particles make their way
into the cerebral nerves,
then dig up and awaken
a sector that is
supposed to stay dormant.
And that is the reason
we have powers?
[Dr. Tsutsumiuchi] For instance,
400 years ago,
we had
an extremely close encounter
and many particles came down.
In Europe, some of those
that inhaled the particles
became witches
with special powers.
The people
who feared the abilities
conducted a witch hunt
and tens of thousands
of ability wielders
were mercilessly slaughtered.
Roughly 12 years ago,
that comet barely grazed
our atmosphere again.
Soon, one after another,
young people began to wield
special abilities.
Yu, he's talking
about us, you know.
[Ayumi] Hmm?
We're developing a vaccine
so that this doesn't happen
again in the future.
Its production has already begun
in Japan.
Sounds like there's
nothing to worry about, then.
No. Japan may be safe,
but that doesn't mean
it's the same
everywhere else in the world.
Witch hunts are still happening
all over.
It never ends.
[Yu] But that has
nothing to do with us.
You can't just dismiss
what's going on, Yu.
The ability wielders overseas
have banded up.
There's always the possibility
that they'll become terrorists
and interfere in world affairs.
Use the vaccine!
[Shunsake]
We can curb the number
of infected that way,
but it doesn't do anything
for the people who already
developed abilities.
Then just make a wonder drug
to counter it or something.
Disappointing.
It would seem
your sharp intellect
doesn't exactly run
in the family, Otosaka.
Unfortunately, it takes
a very long time
to create a new drug.
We don't know what's gonna
happen to us from here on out.
But I promise to protect you
both the best I can.
All right then,
but at the very least,
I'd like Ayumi to regain
her memories about you.
‐Impossible.
‐Why is that?
I got all mine back, didn't I?
We don't know why you were
the only one that regained
memories.
Was there a large factor
somewhere that caused it
or was it just coincidence?
In either case,
it's impossible for now.
Damn it, that's just
so sad for Ayumi.
Starting today, we can make
all new memories as siblings.
Hi, Ayumi.
I'm your oldest brother,
Shunsuke.
It's very nice to meet you.
[Ayumi] Hmm.
OK. Can I call you "Shun"
for short, Big Brother?
‐Yeah.
‐Jeez, that was quick!
[Ayumi giggles]
[Shunsake] You won't be able
to see your school friends
for a while,
but these guys will be
your new friends.
They're also
ability wielders.
Ayumi Otosaka.
It's super nice to meet you.
‐It's nice to meet you too.
‐You're so sweet.
Shichino, why don't you walk
through a wall for starters?
Sure thing.
Try not to wet yourself.
Wow! That's incredible.
The recreation room here
is pretty substantial.
I think you'll find plenty
of fun things to do.
What about music?
Can I listen to How‐Low‐Hello
if I want?
‐Sure can.
‐[Ayumi] All right!
[Shunsake] I'll be
teaching you academics.
‐[Ayumi] OK.
‐[Medoki] You're adorable.
[Ayumi] Thank you very much.
[Yu thinking] I feel like
everyone is keeping
their distance from me.
[gasping]
Huh?
Is everyone gone already?
[Shunsake] They call this one
the Bunei Invasion
and the second one
the Koan Invasion.
[Ayumi] Those are funny names.
[Shunsake] In the literature...
[Medoki] Got a sister complex?
No, not really.
You look so fussy.
‐Big Brother took Ayu
away from you.
‐Wow, Big Brother.
Not true. I'm just bored.
Then you wouldn't mind
hanging out with me.
I want you to play
for me, OK?
Play?
All right, I got a good hand.
Reach!
[Kumagami] Ron.
Double‐value tiles
and little three dragons.
All told, I have 36,000 points.
‐[Yu shrieks]
‐Crazy.
I've never seen someone
bomb out in round one.
You really suck at this game.
Are you sure you're Shunsake's
little brother?
Damn it, let me play one more!
No. I just found
another one.
As usual,
it's rather sudden.
Well, my power doesn't let me
choose when to find them.
It's always quite random.
Believe me, I wish I could use
my ability proactively.
It would make things
so much simpler.
So, what did you find
exactly?
[Kumagami] An ability wielder.
What else?
[Yu] So he didn't have to be
drenched in water!
You're going
to the student council?
‐That's right.
‐Mind if I tag along this time?
Are you really that stupid?
Out of everyone here, you're
in the most danger by far.
You can't just leave.
Oh, right, I forgot about that.
[Yu] I wonder
how Tomori's doing.
Wait, why am I thinking
about her?
[Kumagami] Please head over
to Hoshinoumi Academy.
What's wrong?
Is something the matter?
[driver] No, I'm fine.
Huh? Hey, we were
supposed to take that turn.
Furuki.
[Furuki] I'm sorry, Kumagami.
I have to take you
to a different location.
I don't have a choice.
My family...
They've taken
my family hostage.
You didn't say you had
a family.
If you guys had found out,
I would have had to leave
the syndicate.
That is the rule, yes.
I prided myself on helping you.
It was my greatest honor
and purpose in life.
Please forgive me.
[Kumagami] Sheesh. Guess it's
gonna be one of those days.
[Furuki] Over here. Follow me.
[Kumagami] Sure.
[Furuki] Hey, I brought him!
[Kumagami] Here goes.
[man, Eastern European accent]
Welcome, mighty one.
‐You certainly took
your time getting here.
‐Some foreigners. Oh, brother.
He's here, OK.
Give me back my family.
[man] Not yet. There is one more
thing we need you to do.
We'll contact you later.
Now leave.
That's not what you promised!
If he ever again wants to see
them alive, he'll do it.
You want to see them again,
don't you?
This can't be.
‐[Furuki] I'm sorry.
‐[Kumagami] It's fine.
Furuki, you can just think
about your family.
Sorry!
It's your turn.
Make sure he lives.
[Kumagami] Where... am I?
My head feels woozy.
Looks like they injected
a truth serum.
You're obviously after
information.
[man] We'd like to know
about every other psychic
that you're hiding from us.
Hah. Do your worst.
[chuckles]
I won't have any left soon.
I'll make sure you pay
for my dentures.
[Kumagami groaning]
[screams]
I told them anything
and everything, didn't I?
[retches]
[coughs]
I'm sorry, Shunsuke.
Hyah!
[phone rings]
‐Hello?
‐[man] You are the one
who gathered
all the psychics
in this country, correct?
[Shunsake, thinking]
He's a foreigner.
‐So, what if I am?
‐[foreigner] Kumagami told me
who the strongest psychic
in this country was.
He was very helpful.
[Shunsake thinking]
Kumagami did?
They must have
interrogated him.
Is he still alive?
[foreigner]
Yes, for the moment.
But he's missing
all of his nails and teeth.
What the hell!
What do you want from me?
[foreigner]
We want Yu Otosaka.
That won't happen!
We have kidnapped a psychic
by the name of Nao Tomori.
We would like him in return
for both Tomori and Kumagami.
‐Where at?
‐Furuki will take you there.
Furuki?
I would like Yu Otosaka
to come by himself.
I have heard all about you
from Furuki and Kumagami.
We've been planning
this operation for quite
some time now.
If the plans diverge,
we will assume
you went to the past
to try and change things
and we will kill
Furuki's family.
[click]
[Shunsake] They went
that far.
Make a call.
Furuki's cell.
‐[Furuki] Otosaka.
‐Are you all right?
Did they hurt you, too?
[Furuki] They threatened me.
I'm sorry.
[Shunsake thinking]
Just as I thought.
[Shunsake] How long have they
been threatening you?
[Furuki] Since before we started
building the academy.
[Shunsake, thinking]
That makes it pretty tough.
[Furuki] If I talked, they said
they would kill my family.
I thought about suicide,
but I couldn't leave
my family behind.
So that's...
that's why all this happened.
[Shunsake] It's an error
in my judgment.
There's no need for you
to torment yourself.
I'll make sure
your family's safe.
[Furuki] I'm really sorry.
[Maedomari] So they've made it
out to Japan as well?
[Shichino] How did they get
their hands on Kumagami?
[Shunsake] They've been
threatening Furuki.
It was my mistake.
I knew he had a family
from the start,
but I let him join anyway.
We're dealing
with some evil people.
Then why don't we have
your little brother time‐leap
to before Furuki started getting
threatened by these jerks?
Because it began before
the academy was even built.
If he goes back to that point,
it could mess things up.
Meaning there's
a possibility our syndicate
may not even exist.
They have us backed
into a corner.
Then how about we just have
your little brother
rescue Kumagami?
If we do that, Furuki's family
will be sacrificed.
They're watching us closely.
They'll know if we try it.
[Medoki] How about using
an ability wielder other than
your little brother?
They specifically said Yu
needs to go alone.
If we screw this up,
everyone they've captured
will be killed.
There's nothing
we can do then.
If your brother goes in alone
like they said,
‐it might be our best shot.
‐What?
If we're dealing
with other ability wielders,
we can plunder them.
Even if he screws up,
he can just use time leap
to redo everything
from this point in time.
That way there won't be
any irregularities,
so they won't be able to tell
that he time‐leaped.
We'll bet everything on him.
[Kumagami] So unbecoming.
What a sight.
[straining]
Tomori's captured?
They took out
a ton of security guards.
They’re obviously professionals
from overseas,
and I'm sure that they're armed.
You want me to take them on
by myself?
[Shunsake]
You'll be fine. I know it.
First, you'll need to plunder
all their abilities
and make them drop
all their weapons.
‐Can you do that?
‐Sure thing, if they don't
shoot me first.
The enemy wants you alive.
They won't do anything that
might kill you, understand?
Still, if you get caught,
or if they put Nao and Kumagami
in harm's way,
use your time leap quickly
and come back
to this point in time.
We'll try something else.
And try not to get worked up.
Your collapse power
will trigger,
and then your own life
will be in danger.
Yu, understand?
What's with all this?
Yu?
What is this?
There's no way in hell
I can do something like that!
I'm not some one‐man army,
all right?
I'm just a guy who cheated
his way through school
and got caught in the act!
I'm selfish and cowardly
and only think of myself!
All I ever wanted
was to be popular
and glide through life
without problems!
That's all I am.
What can I...?
[structure rumbling]
[Shunsake] Calm down!
Just focus on my heartbeat.
Concentrate, Yu.
‐Are you calm now?
‐Uh‐huh.
I'm sorry, I was rushing things.
If you think you're in trouble,
just time‐leap back
to this point.
That's all you need
to remember.
We still have some time.
Think it over for a bit.
[Tomori] I gotta say,
you seem like you'd be popular
from just your good looks.
Did you really need to play
the genius
by cheating as much
as possible?
[Yu] We didn't
start off that great.
Some investigation,
of course.
My dream is to film
a video for their band.
That's why I've decided
to stick with you
until this is through
and you're back to normal.
[Yu] It was
the same thing with Ayumi.
You can't have something
once you've lost it.
I will rescue Tomori.
‐I'm ready.
‐So you're OK with it?
Mm‐hmm.
We'll go as far as
we can with you,
so you won't be alone.
If something happens,
we'll rescue you.
[Yu] OK.
‐I'm guessing you're Furuki.
‐[Furuki] Yeah.
[Furuki] Get in.
I brought him!
[Yu] Looks like it's just
these two out in the open.
But they're adults,
not ability wielders.
Then, as I promised, I will
let your family go free.
Here, catch!
[man in suit] That's the key
to the condo.
The location is written
on the tag.
I'm sorry.
This was the only thing
I could do!
[Yu] Let's do this.
They're not armed?
Are you satisfied now?
‐Where is Tomori?
‐[man in suit] Right below us.
Both of them
are in the basement.
Let them go now
and I won't hurt you!
[screeching]
[screams]
I gotta time‐leap.
[mumbling]
Huh?
[man 2] It's pointless.
Even your impressive powers
won't let you travel
to the past
with only one healthy eye.
[Yu growls]
Use collapse if you like,
but your friends in the basement
won't survive it.
Damn it!
Hyaaaaa!
[screams]
‐Damn it, that wasn't necessary!
‐Hurry!
[Yu shrieking]
[Maedomari] Not good.
He's using collapse.
Why isn't he using
time leap?
I have no idea.
What do we do?
[explosions]
No way.
Why the hell are you
just standing there?
‐We have to save them!
‐[Shunsake] Y‐Yeah.
[Shunsake] How does it look?
[Maedomari] Pretty hopeless.
But we still
have to search for them.
‐Nao!
‐Kumagami! Yu!
Shunsuke, over here!
[Maedomari] Are those
the main culprits?
‐[Shunsake] Medoki, please.
‐[Medoki] Right.
I found your brother!
He blocked it
with telekinesis.
He's still alive.
However, they ruined one eye.
So that's why
he couldn't time‐leap.
‐Please, take him somewhere
safe for me.
‐[Shichino] Right.
I swear, if he ends up being OK
but the other two die
because of all this,
I'm gonna be seriously
pissed off.
Kumagami, Nao...
where are you?
[Maedomari] Found them!
They're both here!
Over here!
Kumagami! Kumagami!
You there?
Come on, answer me. Hey!
Kumagami.
[Kumagami, feebly]
Is that you, Shunsuke?
I... tried my best.
Kumagami! Don’t you die!
I won't allow it.
Do you hear me?
You've gotta stay
by my side forever!
I'm afraid that might be
too tall of an order now.
Shut up! Don't talk like that.
You can't go off on your own.
You can't leave me here!
[Kumagami] Shunsuke...
guess the name "Pooh"
was just a lie after all.
Kumagami! Kumagami!
Kumagami!
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]