Hmm.
Hmm. Hmm.
Uh... Hmm.
What is up with me?
Why can't I just pick one?!
[groans]
All right, I'll be going now,
Ayumi.
[door opens, shuts]
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
Oh, hey, good morning.
Oh, right. Good morning.
Let's get going.
Over here.
[man] We could get crepes,
if you like.
Why are we going so early?
The gig is tonight.
I wanna buy
some of the band merch.
You can't do that
after it's over?
Sure, but most of the popular
stuff will be gone by then.
Guess that's how it goes.
I pegged you as
a pretty hardcore fan girl.
I can't believe you didn't wanna
meet Sala yesterday.
I don't have any desire
to buy t‐shirts, hoodies,
or stuff like that.
I want...
their functional and tricked‐out
smartphone case.
It's got an internal battery
and a high‐quality linear
PCM recorder.
OK, I get it.
It sounds awesome.
But you don't want one.
If I did, we'd have
a matching pair.
‐You cool with that?
‐Oh, you're right.
Please make sure
to not buy one.
[Yu thinking]
Well, that was blunt.
I don't know how to take it.
[Yu] The line is huge.
[Tomori] Then we shouldn't
waste time.
‐[man] The line's over here!
‐Come on, let's go get in line.
‐But I'm not buying anything.
‐But you're still here with me.
I don't want to stand there
with no one to talk to.
That's boring.
[Yu] When we first met,
I was sure she hated me.
But now...
inviting me to gigs,
hanging out together.
Why are we getting
all friendly?
[Tomori] What's the matter?
Nothing. I was impressed
by the line.
[Tomori] Well, yeah,
they're loved the world over.
This venue is way too small
for a band of their caliber.
[Yu] She really is
an amazing person.
I got my case!
Look, isn't it epic?
Check out the cool logo
on the back.
Zhiend is such
a figurative art. [giggles]
Uh... yeah, that's for sure.
It's awesome.
I know, right?
[Yu] In the end,
you are a fan girl.
[Tomori] It's so cool!
[cheers, applause]
[rock band plays]
It's starting.
♪ Lying before me ♪
♪ Scene painted in green ♪
♪ I was never found ♪
♪ And I played
hide and seek ♪
♪ There remains
a little scar ♪
♪ On your face
still facing down ♪
♪ To the ground ♪
♪ You hold yourself ♪
♪ And crouch like you've
been wounded ♪
♪ I adored the days ♪
♪ When we just want more things
with no means oh ♪
♪ I adored when you were
always just there for me ♪
♪ By my side ♪
[cheering and applause]
[Yu] What's this strange feeling
I'm getting?
Next up, we have
a special world première,
a song written
just for you, Japan!
"Trigger"!
[cheering]
♪ Come now
heading to the oblivion ♪
♪ To the darkness sink me ♪
♪ Future is lonely
as it seems to be ♪
♪ And I am reaching
from there ♪
[Yu]
I know this song... but this
is my first time hearing it!
♪ My mind is clear now ♪
♪ I feel like I can do
anything ♪
♪ When I want
to do it, yeah ♪
♪ I feel I'm notorious ♪
♪ Do you know
what you can handle? ♪
♪ Do you know me? ♪
♪ Spinning round and around
going back and forth ♪
‐[Yu groans]
‐♪ Will be here as an angel
that's fallen deep ♪
♪ See, there's the dark side
waiting for me ♪
♪ Never end forever ♪
♪ Out on the rim
no need to breathe... ♪
[Yu shrieks]
[song continues on headset]
[shrieks]
[both shriek]
What's the matter, Big Brother?
You scared me!
[Yu] I'm sorry.
I guess Zhiend's new song
really got to me.
They're a pretty amazing band.
Their songs are just
so powerful.
They stick,
no matter what happens.
What about you?
How‐Low‐Hello was How‐Low‐Hello.
Awesome as always.
[woman over loudspeaker]
It is time for dinner
in D Block.
Oh, perfect timing.
I'm starving!
[giggles]
[waltz plays on headset]
[Yu]
It's this old man again.
Why is he here all the time?
[man] Nothing beats classical.
There is no stagnation,
like a mathematical formula.
That girl,
is she your sister?
Yeah.
I see.
I pity you, kid.
[Yu] So there's
a researcher that feels
that way towards us?
[Yu] Why are you here every day?
To get away for a bit.
As a researcher, my hypotheses
are often seen as extraordinary.
I come to lose myself
in thought.
[Yu] I see.
Are you familiar with
the Ptolemaic theory, young man?
[Yu] Well,
I've heard of it, at least.
It's an extraordinary view
by today's standards,
but back then
it was the normal view.
But reality was different.
What do you think happened
‐to the first person
with a different view?
‐Dunno.
He was treated
as a nonconformist
and was shunned
by every one of his peers.
Just like I am now.
[Yu] I see.
All right, we're gonna
have curry today!
Yeah. Chockfull of chemicals
that boost abilities again.
It'll taste like
crappy medicine.
Yeah, maybe, but I still think
its tastiness
will make people happy
and forget about all that stuff.
I wish Big Brother Shun
was here, too.
It would be great
to eat with him.
His unusual ability made him
stand out way too much.
‐He just couldn't‐‐
‐What was his ability again?
Traveling through time,
or time leap.
‐[gasp] That is so amazing!
‐Shhh!
They decided his power
was way too strong
so they're keeping him
imprisoned.
Poor Big Brother Shun.
Yeah, you're right.
So we shouldn't talk about this
ever again, understand?
Thank you for the food!
[Yu] Tastes like
medicine as usual.
They think that my ability
is merely taking over
someone's body
for five seconds,
but there's more to it.
If they'd caught on
to what my true ability is,
I'm sure they'd have taken
my freedom away from me,
just like my big brother.
But if I keep getting
tested like this,
they're bound to find out
eventually.
[Kumagami] Been a while.
Stay still and quiet.
Kumagami, did something happen?
I've finally tracked down
someone with telepathy.
‐[Yu] What? Are you for real?
‐Yeah.
[Kumagami]
They can send and receive.
Amazing.
But they've already
been caught, right?
[Kumagami] Exactly.
First, you need to take over
the guy with the pompadour
to your right.
I found him.
His ability is pulverize,
but his power is limited.
[Yu] Got it.
‐[chuckles]
‐[Yu gasps]
‐[boy 1] Good one.
‐[boy 2] Was that part
of the trick?
[Kumagami] Next is the location
of the one with telepathy.
Take this.
Just make sure to time it right.
You're the only hope we have
now, understand?
If you fail,
they will dispose of you,
and then they'll come for us.
Yeah. I know that.
[Shichino] Oh, man, is Kumagami
really wasting his time
with that idiot right now?
‐Oh, you jealous, Shichino?
‐You know that's not it.
We've been waiting
for this moment for a long time.
A situation like this
is about the only thing
that will make
his little brother serious.
[Shichino] No, man,
he's just overly attached
to his little sister.
He cares for his siblings.
All we can do now is trust him.
I just wonder what our odds are
of actually winning
this little gamble.
If it ain't 100%,
I want no part of it.
There can't be any mistakes.
Does that mean you're actually
gonna use your power
to contribute to us somehow?
We've done our part and managed
to find someone with telepathy
for the team, you know.
Like I've told you,
I'm just waiting for
the perfect moment, OK?
So, it's never
gonna happen then?
‐You piss me off.
‐[door bangs]
Less chitchat, more eating.
Damn it.
I hope this world changes.
I can't take it.
It's time now. Pack up.
Well, so much for smelling
the air outside.
Excuse me.
[guard] Hey, you. Did you accept
something from someone?
Not a thing.
Then you're fine.
[Ayumi] I don't get it.
Why do they treat him
differently?
He do something bad?
He's not as powerful
as big brother,
but he has an ability
that is pretty amazing.
[Yu] All the plans
for saving our brother
are in place.
The only question now is
when to go through with it.
[woman over loudspeaker]
That ends today's program.
All test subjects
other than those called over
must return to their rooms
immediately.
Cool. Guess we'll go back.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
They called me over!
They what? Why didn't you
tell me this earlier?
‐Go back, kid.
‐[Yu] Wait!
This is absurd. My sister
doesn't have abilities.
‐Why is she being called over?
‐[Ayumi] Big Brother Yu!
[structure rattling]
Ayumi! An earthquake?
‐[bell chimes]
‐[woman over loudspeaker]
We have shut D Block down.
Please remain where you are
until you receive...
What the hell's going on?
[Yu] I have a really bad feeling
about this.
Come on, let me outta here!
Hey!
Damn it!
[electronic chime]
It's you.
What just happened?
Do you know where Ayumi is?
Your sister's dormant power
was prematurely forced
into the open.
Her ability was collapse.
They shut D Block down
because half of it caved in
when her ability was set free.
‐Is she OK?
‐She's fine.
But due to the unstable nature
of her power,
they have her restrained
at the moment.
Just like my big brother.
No. After they dissect her,
they’ll get rid of her body.
You don't have time
to stand here!
You can save her
if you use the true ability
you've been hiding.
Plunder: the most powerful
of abilities.
‐How do you know?
‐You don't have time
for me to explain.
[Yu] He's right.
Just go.
All right.
And now they will
dispose of me as well.
[alarm sounding]
[Yu] I'm going
up against someone
with telepathy.
Gotta be mindless, mindless,
mindless!
[telepath] Who is it?
[Yu]
That was in my head?
It's gotta be him,
the telepath.
[telepath] What do you want
with me?
[Yu] I gotta see his face.
[telepath]
What about my face?
[Yu] It's fine.
I'm done here already.
What do you mean?
Hey, stop!
‐[Medoki] Excuse me, sir.
‐Huh?
[guard groans]
[Maedomari] So, uh, I don't need
to erase this guy's memory,
do I?
I hope that's the case...
‐[boy] What's going on?
‐[girl] Let me out!
Let me out!
‐[boy] Shutting down B Block!
‐[woman] I repeat:
there is an emergency
situation in D Block.
All employees arrange
yourselves according...
Damn it!
What's going on out there?
[shrieks]
I don't care who it is,
just tell me!
That voice. I can figure out
the direction, too.
[Yu] Big Brother,
can you hear me? It's Yu!
Yu? You've taken
that kind of power now?
If they find out,
you're done for.
[Yu] I didn't have a choice.
They're about to dissect
Ayumi!
Ayumi! What's she have?
[Yu] An ability strong enough
to destroy this place.
Her too, huh?
[Yu] I'll save you,
Big Brother,
so do your time leap
and change this world for us.
How the hell are you
gonna pull that off?
Damn, I just need light
in my eyes.
‐[alarm beeping]
‐[Yu] What?
[Shunsuke] What's wrong?
‐[Yu] Shichino.
‐Damn it.
Why do I have to do this
for a sister‐complex guy
like you?
[Yu] What the hell‐‐
‐No time to explain!
‐Take my power of permeation.
‐You sure?
I'm telling you, we don't have
any time left. [coughs]
[Yu] I understand.
Don't make me
regret this, OK?
[machine‐gun fire]
I'm sorry, but I know my brother
will change this world!
What the crap.
What's going on here?
‐I'm so tired!
‐[Shunsuke] What's happening?
[Yu] I got Shichino's
ability too.
I'll be right there.
Hold on!
Arrggh!
[gasp]
Finally!
[snarls]
[Shunsuke]
Wish I could stay, Yu.
But I really don't have
any time to waste.
I know. I'm leaving the rest
up to you, Big Brother.
[Shunsuke] Yeah. For the future.
No, for every one of us.
I'm gonna change the world!
[guard] Kill him!
[machine‐gun fire]
[gasps, shrieks]
[gasp] What is it
with you and screaming?
Where are we?
A hospital. You collapsed
during Zhiend's gig.
‐Do you remember that?
‐[Yu] That's right.
Ayumi's gone.
Did you have a bad dream
or something?
[Yu] Dream?
Was what I saw
really a dream?
No. In the past,
Ayumi had said
that she felt like we had
one more member in our family.
[Tomori] It's best if you don't
get up yet.
I think I might have
a big brother.
‐In fact, I'm almost sure of it.
‐What?
[Kumagami] Oh.
So you remember now.
Who are you?
[Kumagami] I find people
with special abilities.
Does this help at all?
[gasp] Water boy!
You're pretty handsome
when you're dry.
You were there, too,
in my dream.
[Kumagami] But this is
the first time
you've seen me like this.
Kumagami, you know all about
my brother, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
Please, tell me everything!
Calm down.
That's what I came here to do.
Come with me quietly,
and I swear,
all the questions you have
will be answered.
After that, you'll rescue
that sister of yours.
[gasp] What did you say?
You're going to save
your sister's life,
simple as that, Yu Otosaka.
But how can I save someone
who's already dead?!
Remember your brother?
If you do, then you already know
what Shunsuke's ability is.
Understood.
Hmm? Just to clarify here,
you mean the Shunsuke?
‐[Kumagami] That's right.
‐[Tomori gasps]
Wait, you're kidding me.
You're his little brother?
‐But you look nothing alike.
‐Does that really matter?
So, uh, can I go see him
as well?
‐It's been a hot minute.
‐How do you know him?
He's the one that guided
my path,
after my big brother became
the way he is.
I met the one person
I could truly trust,
and that's how
I'm here now.
[Yu] So she was
talking about Shunsuke.
That's fine. Follow me.
[Tomori] Thank you very much.
We have to walk from here.
[controller beeps]
Whoa!
This is so cool!
Money is no object here.
[Yu] What is this?
It's kind of
an ability research center.
Didn't that start this mess
in the first place?
Not so.
Stop yapping and follow me.
‐Incredible! Can I record this?
‐[Kumagami] No, of course not.
Nuts!
[controller beeps]
[ding]
[Tomori] Overkill much?
[Kumagami] This is
the last safe place we have.
[Yu] So close.
He's so close to me.
[panel beeping]
Been a while, little bro.
‐I brought him.
‐Yeah, thank you.
That's him?
For real?
He still hasn't remembered?
It seems like he still hasn't
regained all the memories
‐that Maedomari erased.
‐I see.
Erased memories?
What do you mean?
That voice must be Nao.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Yes. I still walk down
the path you set for me.
It really changed my life.
You've been helping out
quite a bit.
‐I'm proud of you.
‐Thank you very much.
[Yu] What the...?
How about you, little bro?
You just gonna stand there
and gawk?
This is
our melodramatic reunion.
‐At least give me a hug.
‐No, thanks.
Still confused.
Lots of questions.
Well, that's a bit lonely.
Though I'm probably reaping
what I've sown.
Guess I should tell
the whole story.
‐Right, Pooh?
‐Yeah.
‐Hmm?
[Toromi and Yu] Pooh?!
[Shunsake, chuckling] Relax.
The story of my time leap's
going to take
quite some time to tell.
[giggles] I'm in
for the long haul.
[Yu] Just what is he going
to tell us?
[woman singing in Japanese]