( banging sounds )
DID I JUST...
ACCELERATE?
Haru:
( gasps )
AM I IN A VIRTUAL WORLD?
HOLD ON!
IS THIS ME?
THIS IS SO...
Man in Black:
WHAT’S WITH THIS GUY?
SEEMS LIKE HE’S SCARED.
Green Girl: THE NAME ISN’T
RINGING A BELL EITHER.
YOU THINK HE’S A NEWBIE?
I DUNNO.
HE’S A METAL-COLORED TYPE,
SO HE SHOULD
BE STRONG.
THOSE AREN’T NPCS.
THEY SEEM LIKE REAL PEOPLE.
( metallic noise )
ARE THEY BURST LINKERS?
OH!
I HAVEN’T FOUGHT IN THE WORLD’S
END STAGE IN AWHILE.
LUCKY ME!
AND EVEN BETTER,
MY OPPONENT IS A NEWBIE.
NOW I’M MEGA LUCKY!
YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND,
YOU ARE GIGA UNLUCKY!
( laughing )
OH NO. IS THIS REALLY
WHAT I THINK IT IS?
I THINK I’M INSIDE OF A...
( gasps )
I AM.
I DON’T STAND A CHANCE!
Hime: ( giggles )
YOU GOT HIT RIGHT AWAY, HUH?
IT’S NOT FUNNY!
I REALLY THOUGHT
I WAS GONNA DIE.
THAT’S WHAT YOU
GET FOR BREAKING
YOUR PROMISE TO ME.
I KNOW. WHEN I LOGGED
ONTO THE GLOBAL NET
I JUST WASN’T THINKING.
WELL, AT LEAST IT WILL
MAKE EXPLAINING THINGS
TO YOU A LITTLE EASIER.
Hime: I’M ASSUMING
YOU’VE FIGURED IT OUT.
WHAT BRAIN BURST ACTUALLY IS?
YEAH. IT’S BASICALLY
JUST A FIGHTING GAME.
BUT ALL OF THE BATTLES
ARE STAGED IN REALITY.
EXACTLY.
( sighs )
THIS IS CRAZY!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
SPEEDING UP BRAINWAVES, HACKING
INTO THE SECURITY CAMERAS...
ALL FOR SOME FIGHTING GAME?
IT’S RIDICULOUS!
HMM, YOU’RE MISSING
THE POINT HERE.
WE BURST LINKERS AREN’T
ACCELERATING JUST SO
WE CAN FIGHT INSIDE A GAME.
WE FIGHT SO WE CAN CONTINUE
TO ACCELERATE.
I’M NOT FOLLOWING.
ACCELERATE,
AND I’LL SHOW YOU.
OKAY.
Both:
BURST LINK.
( grunting )
( gasps )
HMM, SOMETHING WRONG?
NO! NOTHING!
SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
IF YOU LOOK ON THE LEFT SIDE
OF YOUR SCREEN
YOU’LL SEE A NEW DESKTOP ICON
AMONGST THE OTHERS.
Hime: THAT GIVES YOU THE MENU
FOR BRAIN BURST--
AS YOU KNOW,
A FIGHTING GAME.
NOW CLICK ON
THE "MATCHMAKING LIST."
( sighs )
RIGHT NOW IT SHOULD ONLY
HAVE OUR NAMES,
SINCE YOU AND I ARE
THE ONLY BURST LINKERS
CURRENTLY LOGGED
INTO THE LOCAL SCHOOL NET.
OKAY, MISS BLACK LOTUS.
Hime: ALL RIGHT,
NOW CLICK ON MY NAME
AND CHALLENGE ME TO A DUEL.
WHAT?!
WE’RE NOT ACTUALLY GOING
TO FIGHT EACH OTHER.
WE’LL JUST RUN THE CLOCK DOWN
AND CALL IT A DRAW.
GOT IT?
( sighs )
OH, THIS IS
THE TWILIGHT STAGE.
IT’S ACTUALLY
QUITE RARE.
SO. THIS IS
YOUR DUEL AVATAR.
SILVER CROW?
THAT’S A GOOD NAME.
I LIKE THE COLOR,
TOO.
IT’S A GOOD LOOK.
I APPROVE.
I DON’T KNOW.
I THINK IT’S KINDA WIMPY.
CAN IT BE REDESIGNED?
ACTUALLY, WHO ORIGINALLY CAME UP
WITH THIS NAME AND LOOK?
THAT WAS DONE BY YOU.
ME?
THINK BACK. DO YOU
RECALL HAVING A STRANGE
DREAM LAST NIGHT?
YEAH. THE DETAILS
ARE KINDA FUZZY.
BUT I DO REMEMBER IT
BEING SCARY.
THAT WAS THE BRAIN BURST
PROGRAM SCANNING
YOUR SUBCONSCIOUS
WHILE YOU SLEPT.
IT COMPILED THE DATA FROM
ALL YOUR HOPES AND FEARS.
AND THEN IT USED THAT DATA
AS A MOLD FOR YOUR AVATAR.
SO YOU’RE SAYING
THIS WAS ALL MY IDEA?
I WANTED THIS SKINNY
AND SHINY LOOK?
I’M NOT SO SURE.
IT DOESN’T MAKE
YOUR IDEAL IMAGE.
IT’S MORE A REFLECTION
OF ALL YOUR INSECURITIES.
( gasps )
WELL, THEN THAT MEANS
YOUR AVATAR WAS CREATED
BY BRAIN BURST TOO, RIGHT?
NO. ACTUALLY, THIS IS
AN AVATAR THAT I MADE.
IT’S A LONG STORY,
BUT I HAD TO SEAL AWAY
MY ORIGINAL DUEL AVATAR.
SEAL IT AWAY?
UNFORTUNATELY,
IT WAS RATHER UGLY.
A TRULY HIDEOUS THING.
BUT THAT’S ENOUGH ABOUT ME.
THIS MORNING, YOU WERE
ATTACKED AND THEN
BEATEN BY ANOTHER
BURST LINKER.
THINK BACK. DO YOU REMEMBER
HOW THE RESULT SCREEN
READ WHEN
THE FIGHT ENDED?
YEAH, IT HAD MY NAME
AND LEVEL 1.
AND ALSO SOMETHING
CALLED BURST POINTS.
THEY’D GONE
FROM 99 TO 89.
THE BURST POINTS.
THAT’S IT.
THAT’S WHY WE DO THIS.
WHY WE SET FOOT IN THIS RUTHLESS
BATTLEFIELD TIME AND TIME AGAIN.
THE BURST POINTS
REPRESENT HOW MANY TIMES
YOU WILL BE ABLE
TO ACCELERATE.
EACH ACCELERATION
IS EQUAL TO ONE POINT.
SO THEN HOW DO YOU GO
ABOUT GETTING MORE POINTS?
THERE’S ONLY ONE WAY
TO GET MORE POINTS.
BY WINNING FIGHTS.
IF YOUR OPPONENT IS
ON THE SAME LEVEL,
ANY FIGHT YOU WIN OR LOSE
IS TEN POINTS.
THE POWER FROM ACCELERATION
IS UNPARALLELED.
WITH IT YOU CAN EASILY
WIN FIGHTS, ACE TESTS ON
ANY GIVEN SUBJECT, BECOME
A FANTASTICALLY RICH GAMBLER,
OR A CHAMPION ATHLETE.
ONCE YOU’VE TASTED
THE ADVANTAGE IT GIVES YOU,
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO KEEP FIGHTING SO YOU CAN
HOLD ON TO THAT POWER FOREVER.
OKAY, WAIT A SEC.
IF YOU LOSE POINTS EVERY
TIME YOU ACCELERATE OR
GET BEATEN IN A FIGHT,
THAT MEANS A WEAK PLAYER
COULD EVENTUALLY END UP
WITH NO POINTS AT ALL.
WHAT HAPPENS TO ’EM THEN?
THAT IS VERY SIMPLE.
THEY LOSE BRAIN BURST
FOR LIFE.
( gasping )
IT WILL AUTOMATICALLY
UNINSTALL ITSELF
FROM THE USER
AND THE USER CAN
NEVER LOAD IT AGAIN.
EVEN CHANGING
NEURO-LINKERS
WON’T WORK BECAUSE
YOU’RE IDENTIFIED
BY YOUR OWN BRAIN WAVE.
ONCE YOU’VE LOST
ALL YOUR POINTS,
YOU CAN NEVER
ACCELERATE AGAIN.
I’D LOSE BRAIN BURST
FOREVER?
THAT MEANS I’D LOSE
SENPAI, TOO.
HARUYUKI.
IF YOU WANT TO GO BACK
TO YOUR OLD LIFE,
NOW’S THE TIME TO DO IT.
THOSE BULLIES ARE GONE.
THEY WON’T BE COMING BACK.
I PROMISE.
THE CHOICE IS ALL YOURS.
I DON’T THINK YOU REALIZE
JUST HOW MUCH I OWE YOU.
I HAVE TO RETURN THE FAVOR.
HUH?
WHAT YOU DID WAS RESCUE ME
FROM THAT LIVING HELL.
AND I GET THIS FEELING
THAT YOU WANT ME TO DO
SOMETHING IN RETURN.
THAT’S THE ONLY THING
THAT MAKES ANY SENSE.
I MEAN, WHY ELSE WOULD YOU
HAVE SINGLED ME OUT
AND GONE TO ALL
THIS TROUBLE?
I CAN SEE WHY YOU
WOULD THINK THAT.
LOOK...
I KNOW I’M NOT
THE KINDA GUY
A GIRL LIKE YOU
IS USUALLY GONNA
HANG OUT WITH.
I’M JUST A FAT,
UGLY CRYBABY.
I’M A REAL LOSER.
I’M WORTHLESS.
BUT YOU CHOSE ME
AND EVEN CABLE
LINKED WITH ME
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE.
AND LOOK, I’M NOT DELUSIONAL,
I’M NOT GONNA KID MYSELF.
I KNOW THE ONLY REASON
YOU DID IT IS BECAUSE
I’M GOOD AT GAMES.
BUT IF I CAN,
I WANNA BE MORE THAN THAT.
AND, BESIDES, THE TRUTH IS,
WHAT I’M TRYING TO SAY IS
I JUST--I JUST DON’T EVER
WANNA LET YOU DOWN.
THE CHARITY YOU SHOWED ME...
I WANNA REPAY THAT.
SO, I’LL FIGHT.
I’LL DO IT!
I’LL BECOME A BURST LINKER!
Hime: THANK YOU.
BUT DO NOT CALL IT CHARITY.
I AM NOTHING MORE THAN AN
IGNORANT LITTLE SCHOOLGIRL.
I’M A LIVING, BREATHING PERSON
NOT THAT UNLIKE YOURSELF.
YOU’RE THE ONE WHO’S KEEPING
YOUR DISTANCE FROM ME.
DO YOU HONESTLY BELIEVE
THAT THIS GAP BETWEEN US
IS SO GREAT IT CAN
NEVER BE CLOSED?
I DO.
YOU CAN’T BEGIN TO UNDERSTAND
WHERE I’M COMING FROM.
HOW SCARY
IT IS FOR ME.
JUST TO SIMPLY BE NOTICED
AND ACKNOWLEDGED
BY SOMEONE
AS PERFECT AS YOU.
YOU HAVE SINGLE HANDEDLY
TURNED MY LIFE AROUND
AND MADE ME HAPPY.
YOU’RE WHAT SAVED ME
FROM A HORRIBLE HELL.
I COULDN’T ASK
FOR ANYTHING MORE.
I SEE.
WELL, I’M GLAD TO HEAR
YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
TRUTH BE TOLD, I HAVE GOTTEN
MYSELF INTO A LITTLE BIT
OF TROUBLE.
AND I BELIEVE YOU’RE
THE PERSON WHO CAN HELP ME.
I’LL DO EVERYTHING I CAN.
I PROMISE.
JUST TELL ME WHAT YOU NEED.
VERY GOOD.
BUT FIRST YOU MUST LEARN
HOW TO FIGHT.
I DON’T KNOW,
ARE YOU SURE I CAN DO THIS?
YES, I HAVE NO DOUBT
ABOUT IT.
BUT FIRST YOU
NEED TO SIT UP
AND EAT YOUR LUNCH.
IT’S GETTING COLD NOW.
( groaning )
Megumi:
HIME.
I’M SORRY FOR
INTRUDING LIKE THIS,
BUT I’D LIKE
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING
BECAUSE WE’RE ALL
DYING TO KNOW.
IT’S THE SECOND TIME
HE’S HERE.
SO, I WAS JUST CURIOUS
AS TO WHAT EXACTLY
IS GOING ON
WITH THE TWO OF YOU.
WELL, THE TRUTH IS I INVITED HIM
HERE SO I COULD ASK HIM OUT.
BUT HE REJECTED ME.
( screaming )
( gasping )
Students:
WHAT?
WHAT THE HECK
WERE YOU THINKING?
I’M JUST GONNA GET
PICKED ON ALL OVER AGAIN.
THANKS A LOT--
FOR NOTHING!
ALL THAT I DID WAS
SIMPLY TELL THE TRUTH.
AND FROM MY VIEW,
YOU SEEMED TO ENJOY IT.
( screaming )
WHEN DID YOU TAKE
THAT SCREEN SHOT?!
TRASH IT!
YOU SHOULD ACTUALLY
BE PROUD OF THIS.
I HAVE REJECTED
MANY BOYS BEFORE.
BUT YOU’RE THE FIRST
TO REJECT ME.
OKAY, MOVING ON.
UH...
Hime: THE MOMENT
YOU LEAVE THE SCHOOL,
YOU’LL BE CONNECTED
TO THE GLOBAL NET.
ACCELERATE BEFORE
ANYONE ATTACKS YOU.
THEN,
FIND ASH ROLLER
AND CHALLENGE HIM.
GOT IT.
THIS WILL BE YOUR OFFICIAL
DEBUT, SILVER CROW.
GOOD LUCK.
( grunting )
Hime: FIRST,
YOU MUST LEARN HOW TO FIGHT.
FIND YOUR NAME LISTED
BELOW THE ENERGY GAUGE
AND THEN
CLICK ON IT.
OKAY.
THIS IS WHERE YOU FIND OUT WHAT
ABILITIES YOUR DUEL AVATAR HAS.
THIS SAYS I’VE ONLY GOT
A NORMAL PUNCH AND KICK.
AND FOR MY SPECIAL MOVE,
IT’S A HEAD BUTT.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I KNOW THOSE SKILLS SEEM
MEDIOCRE, BUT YOU’LL HAVE
SOMETHING SPECIAL
TO MAKE UP FOR IT,
I’M SURE.
YEAH, BUT...
THE KEY HERE IS YOUR HEART.
IT’S WHAT MADE THAT BODY.
YOU MUST BELIEVE
IN YOURSELF, HARUYUKI.
HE’S HERE!
JUDGING FROM WHAT
YOU’VE TOLD ME,
HE HAS AT LEAST
TWO MAJOR WEAKNESSES.
THE FIRST ONE BEING
THE NOISE FROM THAT BIKE.
THE GUIDE CURSOR WILL TELL
YOU WHERE THE ENEMY’S
GENERAL DIRECTION IS,
BUT THAT NOISE WILL TELL YOU
HIS EXACT LOCATION.
THIS GIVES YOU AN ADVANTAGE.
CAN I REALLY DO THIS?
C’MON, SNAP OUT OF IT!
I’M NOT THE PATHETIC,
CHUBBY KID ARITA NOW!
I’M SILVER CROW,
THE BURST LINKER!
THIS IS THE GAME WORLD
I’VE SPENT SO MANY LONG HOURS
PLAYING AND DOING EVERYTHING
I CAN TO PERFECT MY SKILL.
THIS IS MY WORLD!
HUH?
( screams )
I--I DID IT!
( groans )
I HAVE TO KEEP MOVING!
Hime: AS FOR ASH ROLLER’S
SECOND WEAKNESS...
BY THE WAY HIS DUEL AVATAR
IS DESIGNED,
NEARLY ALL OF ITS POTENTIAL
IS WRAPPED UP IN THAT BIKE.
THAT MEANS THE COMBAT ABILITY
OF THE RIDER
HIMSELF SHOULD BE
CLOSE TO ZERO.
OH, MY FUCKING GOD!
SO, IF YOU MANAGE TO
DAMAGE HIM BADLY EARLY ON,
ALL YOU’LL HAVE TO DO IS WAIT
FOR THE TIME TO RUN OUT.
Green Girl:
WELL, NOW. THE KID’S
NOT THAT BAD.
Man in Black:
YEAH, HE’S MUCH
BETTER THAN BEFORE.
I WONDER WHO
HIS GUARDIAN IS?
DON’T KNOW, BUT IF
HE WINS THIS, I’LL ADD
HIM TO MY WATCH LIST.
GO GET HIM, KID.
( laughs )
I DON’T KNOW.
I DOUBT IT’LL BE THAT EASY.
( gasps )
WAIT. WHAT ARE YOU
TRYIN’ TO DO?
DON’T THINK YOU’VE WON JUST YET,
NEWBIE.
I’M ABOUT READY TO MAKE YOU
DANCE TO THE BEAT OF MY BIKE!
LET’S ROLL!
AHH!
ISN’T THAT LIKE, CHEATING?
DAMN, EVEN A SLIGHT GRAZE LIKE
THAT CAUSES YOU TO LOSE POINTS?
THAT’S HARSH!
THANKS TO THAT BEAT DOWN I WAS
ABLE TO PUT ON YOU THIS MORNING,
I’VE NOW MOVED UP
AND REACHED LEVEL 2.
THEN, I TOOK THAT
LEVEL-UP BONUS I GOT
AND CASHED IT IN FOR SOME
AWESOME WALL-CLIMBING POWERS.
PRETTY SWEET CHOICE BY ME,
RIGHT?
BUT FOR YOU...
IT MEANS TERA UNLUCKY!
AHH!
Hime: IF YOUR FIRST ATTACK
FAILS TO BE SUCCESSFUL
OR YOU CAN’T HIDE,
THE CHANCES OF YOU WINNING
THIS FIGHT ARE VERY SMALL.
AND HERE’S WHY.
BURST LINKER NAMES START
WITH A COLOR,
IT’S A SORT OF SHORTHAND.
AN INDICATION OF THE KIND
OF QUALITIES YOU POSSESS.
SILVER SAYS A LOT ABOUT YOU.
IT’S A VERY RARE
AND POWERFUL COLOR.
YOU ARE RESISTANT TO SLASH
AND PIERCE ATTACKS,
AS WELL AS FIRE AND POISONS.
YOU’RE ALSO QUITE GOOD
AT CLOSE RANGE COMBAT.
BUT YOU’RE VULNERABLE TO
CORROSION AND BLUNT ATTACKS.
I SEE.
ASH ROLLER’S FAINT COLOR IMPLIES
A UNIQUE ATTACK STYLE.
IF I WERE TO GUESS AT
WHAT HIS STRENGTH IS,
I’D SAY IT’S DIRECT BLOWS
FROM HIS BIKE.
WHICH MEANS AGAINST
THAT SORT OF ATTACK
YOUR ARMOR WILL BE
VIRTUALLY USELESS.
THIS LEAVES YOU
WITH ONLY ONE OPTION.
YOU MUST EVADE HIM
UNTIL TIME RUNS OUT.
EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
( screams )
DAMN IT!
YOU EVEN FEEL THE PAIN.
THAT HURT.
( wild laughing )
WHAT? NO COUNTER ATTACK,
FUCK-FACE?
WELL, THEN I GUESS
I GET TO GO AGAIN.
COME ON.
I NEED SOMETHING.
SOMETHING THAT’S GONNA SAVE ME.
LIKE A SECRET WEAPON.
OF COURSE!
MY SPECIAL MOVE!
( murmuring )
( yelling )
All:
OH!
( laughing )
OH, WELL.
GUESS IT’S OVER.
DAMN IT.
DAMN IT!
THIS IS MY WORLD.
I’M SUPPOSED TO BE A HERO HERE!
THIS SUCKS! MY SPECIAL MOVE
DIDN’T EVEN CONNECT.
THERE’S NO WAY I CAN WIN
WITH THIS WEAK AVATAR!
IT’S IMPOSSIBLE!
I CAN’T!
THE KEY HERE IS YOUR HEART.
IT’S WHAT MADE THAT BODY
YOU MUST BELIEVE
IN YOURSELF, HARUYUKI.
LISTEN, IF THERE’S
ONE PERSON IN THIS WORLD
WHO I FIND IT HARD TO
BELIEVE IN, THAT WOULD BE ME.
I MEAN COME ON, THIS AVATAR
EVEN LOOKS LIKE A PILE OF TIN.
IF I GOT YOUR HOPES UP,
I’M SORRY.
JUST FORGET ABOUT ME
AND MOVE ON.
THAT’S ENOUGH.
YOU ARE MISSING THE POINT.
STRENGTH ISN’T SOLELY
DEFINED BY THE NUMBER
OF VICTORIES YOU HAVE WON.
UNFORTUNATELY, BY THE TIME
THE TIME I REALIZED THIS,
IT WAS ALREADY TOO LATE.
Haru:
NO. I CAN’T GIVE UP.
EVEN IF I LOSE,
I’VE GOTTA KEEP ON GOING
AND CLAWING MY WAY BACK
’TIL THE BITTER END.
IF I’M GOIN’ DOWN,
I’M GOIN’ DOWN FIGHTING!
THAT’S WHAT A PAWN
IS SUPPOSED TO DO!
( laughing )
COME ON, THINK.
I’VE PLAYED HOURS
AND HOURS OF GAMES.
IF THIS IS JUST
LIKE THE REAL WORLD,
THEN THAT BIKE’S GOTTA
HAVE A WEAK POINT.
AN INTERNAL COMBUSTION ENGINE
FROM THE 20TH CENTURY.
WHAT’S ITS WEAKNESS?
THINK!
THAT’S IT!
( laughing )
READY TO DANCE SOME MORE?!
JUST THIS ONCE, SILVER CROW,
MOVE FOR ME!
WE’VE GOTTA BE
FASTER THAN HIM!
EVEN IF I CAN’T BELIEVE
IN MYSELF,
( gasping )
( grunting )
I CAN AT LEAST BELIEVE IN
EVERYTHING SHE’S SAID!
( laughing )
DUMB ASS! DO YOU REALLY
THINK A LITTLE SHIT STAIN
LIKE YOU CAN STOP A
MONSTER BIKE LIKE THIS?!
( grunting )
( laughing )
YOU BETTER LET GO KID, OR YOU’RE
GONNA BE GROUND DOWN TO A NUB.
( yelling )
( laughing )
ALMOST THERE.
IT’S ALL OVER!
OKAY, HERE I GO!
( gasping )
HUH? WHA...
( growling )
WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS?!
WHOA!
PRETTY SMART.
ALL BIKES WITH INTERNAL
COMBUSTION ENGINES HAVE
REAR WHEEL DRIVE.
SO IF YOU HOLD THE BACK END UP
THEY BECOME TOTALLY USELESS.
ASH ROLLER IS NOW LIKE A TURTLE
THAT’S BEEN FLIPPED ON ITS BACK.
I’M IMPRESSED.
WELL PLAYED, SILVER CROW.
YOU’RE ADDED TO THE LIST.
I’M ROOTING FOR YA’.
( sigh of relief )
PUT ME DOWN, YA’ LITTLE
FART BREATHER!
LET GO OF ME ALREADY.
FORGET THAT.
TRY USING YOUR FRONT TIRE
IF YOU WANNA
GO SOMEWHERE.
( growling )
DON’T MESS WITH ME!
YOU SON OF A BITCH,
YOU’RE GONNA PAY!
( sighs )
YOU DID IT,
SILVER CROW!
I HAVE TO ADMIT,
I THOUGH YOU WERE DONE FOR.
YEAH, I KNOW.
MORE THAN ONCE I THOUGHT
THE SAME THING MYSELF.
DON’T BE SO MODEST.
YOU EARNED THAT VICTORY.
NOT REALLY.
SO, WERE YOU ABLE TO
GET YOUR POINTS BACK?
YEAH, I GOT ’EM BACK
AND THEN SOME MORE.
I GUESS THAT’S BECAUSE HE WAS
UP TO LEVEL TWO ON THIS ROUND.
( laughs )
OF COURSE. SO THAT
EXPLAINS WHY HE WAS ABLE
TO CLIMB UP THOSE WALLS.
I KNOW, WHEN I SAW THAT
I COULDN’T BELIEVE IT!
IT WAS A GREAT WIN, HARUYUKI.
NICELY DONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
WE SHOULD GO CELEBRATE.
WHERE WOULD YOU LIKE...
( gasping )
( yells )
CHIYU!
JUST WHAT DO YOU
WANT WITH HARU?
DON’T YOU SEE WHAT
YOU’VE DONE?
BECAUSE YOU WENT
AND EGGED SOMEONE
ON YESTERDAY,
HARU HERE
GOT BEATEN UP AGAIN.
AND NOW YOU’RE
STILL DOING IT.
YOU’RE MAKING
A SPECTACLE OF HIM
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE.
WHAT SORT OF PLAN
ARE YOU HATCHING?
OH...
( gasping )
( screaming )
♪
NEXT STAGE:
"INVESTIGATION."
A MYSTERIOUS ENEMY
IS STALKING KUROYUKIHIME.
IN THE END, WHO WILL
HARUYUKI’S SEARCH UNCOVER?