( sighs )
HEY, TAKU.
HUH?
THAT NOMI KID...
DO YOU THINK HE’S
A BURST LINKER?
SO THAT’S WHAT’S
BEEN BUGGING YOU TODAY.
LOOK, THE VERY SECOND
I THOUGHT HE ACCELERATED,
I ACCELERATED AS WELL.
BUT IT’S WEIRD....
WHEN I CHECKED
THE MATCHING LIST,
HIS NAME WASN’T ON IT.
Chiyuri: OH, GREAT.
( grunts )
YOU’RE EATING THAT
JUNK FOOD AGAIN?
I’VE BEEN TELLING YOU THIS
FOR AGES, HARU.
YOU REALLY NEED TO LEARN
HOW TO COOK FOR YOURSELF.
YEAH, BUT I SORT OF
DID COOK THIS.
I MEAN, IT’S NOT TAKE-OUT.
ALL YOU DID WAS TAKE IT
OUT OF THE BOX AND REHEAT IT.
YEAH, BUT I SERVED IT
ON A PLATE.
THAT STILL DOESN’T
COUNT AS COOKING.
( sighs )
I FIGURED THIS WOULD HAPPEN...
SO I GOT MY MOM
TO MAKE HER FAMOUS LASAGNA.
AM I THE BEST, OR WHAT?
( both gasping )
WAIT, YOU DIDN’T COOK THAT
YOURSELF, EITHER.
YEAH, AND?
NOTHING!
THANKS A LOT!
THAT WAS VERY NICE.
Taku: THAT WAS AMAZING.
YOUR MOM IS SUCH
A GREAT COOK.
SHE SHOULD OPEN UP
A RESTAURANT.
YOU WOULD THINK,
BUT ACTUALLY,
IT WOULD NEVER WORK.
WHEN SHE ISN’T
COOKING SOMETHING FOR MY DAD,
SHE ONLY EVER
PUTS IN HALF THE EFFORT.
THIS IS HALF
AND IT’S THIS GOOD?
NO, THIS IS MORE THAN THAT.
I’D SAY IT’S HER
AT ABOUT 95%.
SEE, MY MOM THOUGHT SHE
WAS COOKING THIS MEAL
FOR THE GUY WHO’S GONNA
BECOME MY FUTURE HUSBAND.
SHE’S SO SILLY.
I MEAN, WE’RE STILL
JUST KIDS, RIGHT?
( yelling )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( indistinct singing )
♪ AND WATCH IT GO SLOW ♪
♪ SLOWLY OPEN UP MY EYES ♪
( indistinct singing )
( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER LET IT GO,
NEVER LOSE MY WAY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
Chiyuri: WHAT? REALLY?
YOU THINK NOMI
IS A BURST LINKER?!
WELL, HE DIDN’T
APPEAR ON THE MATCHING LIST,
BUT IT LOOKED LIKE
DURING OUR MATCH...
THAT HE WAS ACCELERATING.
NOW THAT YOU SAY THAT,
YOU’RE RIGHT.
WHENEVER HE
DODGED YOUR ATTACKS,
IT WAS LIKE HE WAS ABLE
TO SEE THEM COMING.
IT WAS MORE THAN THAT.
IT WAS LIKE HE WAS ABLE
TO MOVE HIS REAL BODY
WHILE HE WAS
IN AN ACCELERATED STATE.
( grunts )
( no audible dialogue )
WAIT. IT WAS JUST LIKE
PHYSICAL FULL BURST.
WHAT’S THAT MEAN?
IT’S A FORBIDDEN COMMAND
THAT ONLY LEVEL NINE LINKERS
CAN USE.
IF YOU USE IT, YOU LOSE 99%
OF YOUR TOTAL POINTS.
BUT YOUR REAL BODY CAN THEN
MOVE A HUNDRED TIMES FASTER.
SERIOUSLY?
YEAH, BUT KEEP IN MIND
THERE ARE ONLY SEVEN PEOPLE
WHO’VE EVER REACHED LEVEL NINE.
AND NONE OF THEM HAD ANY REASON
TO BE AT THAT PRACTICE MATCH.
BESIDES, EVEN IF NOMI DOES
TURN OUT TO BE A LEVEL NINE,
WHY WOULD HE RISK
USING 99% OF HIS TOTAL POINTS
FOR WHAT WAS BASICALLY
A PRACTICE MATCH?
IT DOESN’T MAKE ANY SENSE.
UNLESS HE WASN’T
USING PHYSICAL FULL BURST
AT ALL,
BUT SOMETHING FAR LESS RISKY.
HUH? W-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
( grunts softly )
( sighs )
PHYSICAL BURST.
( gasps )
NO WAY.
YOUR BODY DOESN’T ACCELERATE,
BUT YOUR CONSCIOUSNESS
DOES BECOME TEN TIMES FASTER.
IT LASTS FOR THREE SECONDS.
SO IF YOU USE THAT, THEN...
THEN DODGING YOUR OPPONENT’S
ATTACKS IN A FIGHT
OR EVEN HITTING A HOME RUN
IN BASEBALL BECOMES PRETTY EASY.
AND OF COURSE, IT GIVES YOU
AMAZING RESULTS IN A KENDO
TOURNAMENT.
EVERYTHING BECOMES EASY
FOR YOU.
JUST LIKE IT WAS FOR ME.
UH--UM, TAKU?
( sighs )
SEIJI NOMI IS EXACTLY
LIKE I WAS A YEAR AGO.
WHAT RIGHT DO I HAVE TO SIT HERE
AND COMPLAIN ABOUT GETTING BEAT
BY HIM WHEN--OW!
( groaning softly )
YOU’RE WRONG!
YOU ARE NOT THE SAME!
CHI, BUT--BUT I...
WHEN YOU WERE
WINNING ALL THOSE MATCHES,
YOU WERE DOING IT
FOR US, RIGHT?
WHENEVER YOU’D WIN,
THE FIRST THING YOU WOULD DO
IS FIND ME IN THE CROWD
AND THEN SMILE AND WAVE.
( grunts )
MM-HMM.
BUT THIS GUY IS DIFFERENT.
IF YOU ASK ME,
THE ONLY PERSON THIS NOMI KID
IS FIGHTING FOR IS HIMSELF.
AFTER HE WON,
HE JUST SORT OF SAT THERE
AND LOOKED ALL SMUG.
THAT’S WHY I’M SAYING
HE’S NOT LIKE YOU AT ALL.
( sighs )
YEAH. SHE’S RIGHT, TAKU.
AND YOU’RE A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT PERSON NOW.
LISTEN, WHAT WE HAVE
TO DO NEXT IS FIGURE OUT
HOW HE’S BEEN KEEPING HIS NAME
OFF THE MATCHING LIST.
AND THEN WE CAN GO
AND THRASH HIM IN A DUEL.
EXACTLY. AND NO MATTER
HOW BADLY YOU GET BEATEN UP,
I’LL KEEP ON HEALING YOU.
THANKS A LOT, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, I’LL SEE WHAT I CAN
FIND OUT ABOUT THIS NOMI GUY
DURING OUR NEXT CLUB PRACTICE.
( metal rings )
NICE JOB, SILVER CROW,
CYAN PILE.
SAME TO YOU.
I HAVE TO RUN.
I’M ON A SHORT BREAK
DURING THE MIDDLE
OF KENDO PRACTICE.
SORRY.
MASTER, IF I DON’T
SEE YOU BEFORE YOU
LEAVE FOR OKINAWA TOMORROW,
HAVE A GOOD TRIP.
HE’S REALLY INTO HIS
KENDO CLUB, ISN’T HE?
( breathes heavily )
YEAH, I GUESS HE HIS.
ACTUALLY, ABOUT THAT...
I NEED TO TELL YOU SOMETHING
REGARDING THE KENDO CLUB.
HUH?
( sparring in distance )
( grunts )
I’M SORRY.
IS SOMETHING WRONG, SENPAI?
NOT AT ALL.
I’M JUST TRYING
TO LEARN THE SECRETS
BEHIND YOUR INCREDIBLE
SPEED AND STRENGTH.
I JUST GOT A LITTLE
LUCKY LAST TIME.
THAT WAS IT.
NOT TRUE.
THE WAY YOU MOVED
WAS REALLY QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
THANK YOU.
BUT YOU’RE RATHER
IMPRESSIVE YOURSELF.
I’D HEARD A LOT OF RUMORS
ABOUT YOU BEFORE OUR MATCH--
ABOUT HOW GOOD YOU ARE.
BUT THAT WAS AT YOUR
PREVIOUS SCHOOL,
BEFORE YOU DECIDED
TO TRANSFER HERE.
( gasps )
YOU KNOW, IF YOU STILL
FOUGHT AS HARD AS YOU USED TO,
LIKE YOU DID BACK AT YOUR
OLD SCHOOL,
THEN I BET I WOULD
BE NO MATCH FOR YOU.
Kuroyukihime: ARE YOU
POSITIVE ABOUT THIS?
THIS SEIJI NOMI,
A FIRST-YEAR STUDENT,
ACCELERATED DURING A MATCH?
WELL WE DON’T
HAVE ANY HARD PROOF YET.
AND HIS NAME DIDN’T SHOW UP
ON THE MATCHING LIST, EITHER.
IT’S PROBABLY
BEING MASKED BY SOME SORT
OF ILLEGAL PROGRAM.
BUT EVEN IF HE
DID DO THIS, WHY?
WHAT DOES HE WANT?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I GUESS THE ONLY WAY
TO FIND OUT...
IS FOR US TO CHALLENGE HIM
TO A DUEL
AND THEN ASK HIM OURSELVES.
I SUPPOSE.
WHEN IT COMES
TO BEING A BURST LINKER,
IT ALL STARTS WITH A DUEL.
I’D PREFER IT
IF I WERE THE FIRST
TO FIGHT HIM.
BUT I HAVE TO GO
ON THIS TRIP TOMORROW,
AND WON’T BE BACK FOR A WEEK.
PERHAPS I SHOULD
FAKE AN ILLNESS AND STAY.
( gasps )
NO, NO, NO!
DON’T DO THAT!
( gasps )
YOU HAVE TO GO.
IT’S A SCHOOL TRIP.
WE’LL FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO DEAL WITH NOMI.
DON’T WORRY.
FINE, THEN.
BUT JUST DON’T
DO ANYTHING RASH.
I WON’T. I PROMISE.
WELL, I GUESS THIS
MEANS THAT YOU NOW
KNOW EVERYTHING THERE
IS TO KNOW ABOUT THE PHYSICAL
BURST COMMAND.
I WON’T SAY, "DON’T USE IT,"
BUT IN NEGA NEBULOUS,
USING IT TO WIN SOME SORT
OF SPORTING EVENT
IS STRICTLY PROHIBITED.
NO WAY!
I’D NEVER DO THAT!
LOOK, INSTEAD OF SPENDING FIVE
POINTS FOR JUST THREE SECONDS,
I’D MUCH RATHER GIVE UP
TEN POINTS
TO DIVE INTO THE UNLIMITED
NEUTRAL FIELD.
OH, BY THE WAY,
DID YOU DECIDE WHAT IT IS
YOU WANT ME TO BRING YOU
FROM OKINAWA?
YEAH, WELL,
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT,
AND I DON’T WANT YOU
TO HAVE TO LUG AROUND
ANYTHING BIG THE WHOLE TIME.
SO I’D BE HAPPY IF YOU WOULD
JUST SHOW ME SOME OF THE MOVIES
YOU RECORDED WHILE YOU
WERE THERE.
REALLY?
THAT’S ALL YOU WANT?
ARE YOU SURE?
( thinking )
WELL, TO BE EXACT,
WHAT I REALLY WANT
ARE MOVIES OF YOU.
TO BE EVEN MORE EXACT,
SUPER-HIGH-RESOLUTION VIDEOS
OF YOU IN BIKINIS AND STUFF.
AND, IF YOU COULD SHOW THEM
TO ME THROUGH CABLE LINK WITH
A SHORT, 30-CENTIMETER CABLE--
OKAY, I’LL RECORD LOTS
OF MOVIES AND SEND THEM TO YOU.
( whimpers )
I’LL RECORD ALL THE OKINAWAN
FOOD I EAT.
SOUND GOOD?
UH--
( sighs )
Haru: THIS ISN’T REALLY
WHAT I HAD IN MIND, SENPAI.
( grunts softly )
WHY COULDN’T I
BE IN THE SAME GRADE AS HER
SO I COULD
GO ON THIS TRIP, TOO?
( electronic tones )
( grunts )
Female Computerized Voice:
YOU’VE GOT MAIL.
( grunts )
IS IT FROM SENPAI?
( beeping )
Taku: MORNING, HARU.
AW, IT’S TAKU.
SORRY TO TAKE SO LONG
TO TELL YOU IF I
FOUND ANYTHING ON NOMI.
I TRIED TO CONNECT TO HIS NEURO
LINKER AND SEE IF BRAIN BURST
WAS INSTALLED ON IT,
BUT I DIDN’T GET A CHANCE
TO DO IT.
BUT I DID FIND OUT
SOMETHING ELSE.
THERE WAS ANOTHER STUDENT
AT OUR SCHOOL NAME YUICHI NOMI.
I FOUND HIM
IN THE GRADUATION PHOTO.
HE’S THREE YEARS
OLDER THAN US.
( grunts )
IT’S PROBABLY HIS BROTHER.
IF NOMI IS A BURST LINKER,
THEN HIS BROTHER
MIGHT BE HIS GUARDIAN.
WHAT’S THE LAG?
( electronic humming
and beeping )
SO HE’S AN ALUM
FROM OUR SCHOOL, HUH?
WAIT A SEC.
THAT’S WEIRD.
I’VE NEVER HEARD OF THERE
BEING ANOTHER BURST LINKER
AT OUR SCHOOL THAT’S OLDER
THAN KUROYUKIHIME SENPAI.
ARE YOU REALLY
A BURST LINKER?
( sparring in distance )
Takagi: HEY! NOMI!
WE’RE NOT FINISHED YET.
HEY!
YOU PUNK.
DON’T GET ALL COCKY
JUST ’CAUSE YOU MADE THE TEAM!
JERK!
( gasps )
( all gasping)
A PROPER MEMBER OF THE KENDO
CLUB SHOULD KNOW BETTER
THAN TO EVER
THROW HIS SHINAI SWORD.
BUT...THAT’S PROBABLY
WHY YOU CAN’T MAKE THE TEAM.
( laughs )
HE JUST ACCELERATED!
THERE’S NO OTHER EXPLANATION.
NOMI HAS TO BE
A BURST LINKER!
NOW I JUST NEED
TO GET SOME PROOF.
( groaning, whimpering )
HE’S HEADING TO THE SHOWERS.
( panting )
( gasps )
( thinking )
HERE’S MY CHANCE
TO GET SOME HARD PROOF.
( gulps )
( grunts )
( gasps )
HIS NEURO-LINKER.
IF I CABLE LINK TO THIS,
I CAN SEARCH
FOR THE BRAIN BURST PROGRAM.
( grunts softly )
( gulps )
( sighs )
HUH?
WAIT, IS THIS...?
( gasps )
( Chiyuri gasps )
CHI--
CHIYU?
( whimpering )
HARU, WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU DOING
IN THE GIRLS’ SHOWERS?
WHAT?! THE GIRLS’ SHOWERS?!
NO WAY!
I’M SURE THAT I--
( grunts )
( gasping )
HARU!
( girls laughing )
Girl 1: I’M EXHAUSTED.
( yells )
Girl 2: YEAH, ME, TOO.
I CAN’T WAIT
TO GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
RIGHT?
WANNA GO GRAB A BITE?
SURE. THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
( gasping )
Chiyuri: STAND STILL
AND DON’T SAY ANYTHING.
Girl 1: AH, GEEZ,
I FEEL SO GROSS.
Girl 2: YEAH, I KNOW--I REALLY
NEED TO HIT THE SHOWERS.
( whispers )
If they see you,
you’ll get expelled.
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
I KNOW I
CHECKED THOSE SIGNS.
HOLD ON. WAS THAT
AN ELECTRONIC VISUAL MASKING?
HUH? A WHAT?
IT OVERRIDES THE VISUAL FIELD
IN YOUR NEURO-LINKER.
YOU CAN DO THINGS
LIKE SWITCH SIGNS
SO YOU THINK YOU’RE
ENTERING THE BOYS’ SHOWER
WHEN YOU’RE REALLY
ENTERING THE GIRLS’.
NOMI TOTALLY SET A
TRAP FOR ME.
Girl 2: HEY, CHI,
ARE YOU STILL IN THERE?
( gasps )
UH, YEAH. I CAN’T
BELIEVE THAT WORKOUT TODAY.
I GOT SUPER SWEATY.
I KNOW, RIGHT?
THAT COACH WAS PUSHING US
WAY TOO HARD FOR THE UPCOMING
DISTRICT QUALIFIERS.
Girl 1: ISN’T THAT WATER
WAY TOO HOT FOR YOU, CHI?
IT’S REALLY STEAMY IN HERE.
Chiyuri: NO, I LOVE IT
HOT LIKE THIS.
IT’S GOOD FOR YOUR
CIRCULATION, TOO.
OH, SHUT UP.
YOU’RE STARTING TO SOUND LIKE
MY GRANDMA NOW.
( giggling )
( other shower turns on )
I’M SORRY.
I’M SO SORRY.
I TOTALLY SCREWED UP.
NOW’S YOUR CHANCE.
( grunts )
OKAY, GO!
( panting )
( grunts, whimpers )
( sighs )
( groans softly )
I’M SORRY!
I REALLY MEAN IT!
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
( Chiyuri growls )
( whimpering )
YOU’RE PICTURING ME
NAKED AGAIN, RIGHT?!
NO! I WASN’T!
I SWEAR I WASN’T!
( grunts )
LET’S MOVE ON.
THAT ELECTRONIC
VISUAL THINGY--
WHEN DID HE HAVE A CHANCE
TO DO IT?
WELL...I DON’T KNOW.
WHY’S EVERYONE
ACTING SO CRAZY?
I MEAN, IT’S JUST A GAME.
IT’S INSANE.
LOOK, AT ITS CORE,
BRAIN BURST IS A GAME.
BUT IT’S REALLY
MORE THAN THAT.
SEE, FOR PEOPLE LIKE NOMI
WHO USE ACCELERATION
TO UP THEIR STATUS
IN THE REAL WORLD,
IT’S EVERYTHING.
AND THEY’LL DO WHATEVER
THEY HAVE TO
TO PROTECT THEIR POWER.
HARU, I REALLY
DON’T LIKE THIS!
YOU GUYS ARE TAKING THIS THING
WAY TOO FAR!
YOU KEEP SAYING IT’S A GAME,
BUT YOU, TAKU, AND NOMI
DON’T SEEM TO BE HAVING
ANY FUN AT IT.
NO, THAT ISN’T TRUE AT ALL!
AND TO BE HONEST, I THINK THAT
THANKS TO BRAIN BURST,
I’VE ACTUALLY CHANGED A BIT.
IT’S WHAT LET TAKU AND ME
CONFRONT EACH OTHER HONESTLY.
AND I ALSO THINK THAT
BECAUSE OF THIS GAME,
I’M A LITTLE LESS
OF A COWARD NOW, TOO.
YEAH, WELL
I GUESS THAT PART’S TRUE,
’CAUSE I HAVE NO DOUBT
THAT IF THE OLD YOU
HAD SEEN ME NAKED,
YOU WOULD’VE AVOIDED ME
FOR AN ENTIRE MONTH
AND NEVER HAD THE GUTS
TO APOLOGIZE FOR IT.
AH!
I AM REALLY SORRY.
I MEAN IT.
I’M SUCH AN IDIOT.
IT’S ALL MY FAULT.
IT’S OVER!
JUST FORGET ABOUT IT!
BUT IF I EVER FIND OUT
THAT YOU MENTIONED A WORD
OF THIS TO TAKKUN,
THEN I PROMISE I REALLY
WILL KILL YOU.
OKAY, I WON’T TELL TAKU.
IF YOU DO,
I’LL TELL KUROYUKI SENPAI
THAT YOU’RE A DIRTY PERV.
( whimpering )
Taku: HEY, WHAT’S WRONG?
HUH?!
EVER SINCE I SAW YOU
THIS MORNING, YOU’VE
BEEN ACTING KINDA WEIRD.
REALLY? H-HAVE I?
UH, ACTUALLY--
MMM?
( groans )
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, IT’S JUST...MY TUMMY.
IT’S BEEN KIND OF MESSED UP
ALL MORNING.
HMM?
I THINK I’D BETTER
HEAD TO THE RESTROOM.
( grunts softly )
Female Computerized Voice:
YOU’VE GOT MAIL.
( breathing heavily )
IT’S FROM NOMI.
IS THIS WHERE HE’S
TALKING ABOUT?
( gasps )
GAME OVER, ARITA SENPAI.
OR SHOULD I SAY,
"SILVER CROW"?
( gasps )
I WIN.
AND THEREFORE, YOU LOSE.
WAIT! NOBODY’S
WON ANYTHING YET!
( panting )
( grunts softly )
WE HAVEN’T EVEN
FOUGHT EACH OTHER.
AND THE ONLY REASON FOR THAT
IS BECAUSE YOU’VE DONE SOMETHING
TO HIDE YOUR NAME
ON THE MATCHING LIST.
WHAT’S THE POINT
OF SOME SILLY DUEL?
THERE’S NO NEED FOR IT.
NOT AS LONG AS I HAVE THIS.
( electronic ringing )
( sighs )
OPEN IT.
IT’S OKAY.
AND THIS FILE DOESN’T
COME WITH A VIRUS.
I PROMISE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "THIS FILE"?
( gasps )
WAIT, DID YOU PUT THAT
ELECTRONIC VISUAL MASK
ON THE CLASS PHOTO?
I MAY HAVE INSTALLED A PROGRAM
IN THE NAMETAG
THAT MESSES A BIT
WITH YOUR VISUAL FIELD.
AND ALTHOUGH YOU
FIGURED IT OUT,
YOUR POOR BEST FRIEND
DIDN’T AT ALL.
( gasps )
ALL RIGHT. HOW DID YOU
TAKE THIS FOOTAGE?
SEE? I WENT ALL OLD-SCHOOL.
I STRATEGICALLY PLANTED IT
IN THE GIRLS’ SHOWER ROOM.
ACTUALLY, IT WAS ONE
OF TEN TRAPS
I HAD SET AROUND THE SCHOOL.
THIS ONE WAS THE LONG-SHOT.
WHO WOULD’VE THOUGHT IT
WOULD ACTUALLY WORK?
CRAZY, RIGHT?
( laughing )
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
ARE YOU REALLY THAT DESPERATE
TO GET RID OF SILVER CROW?
WHAT? IS YOUR MASTER PLAN
TO TRY AND GET ME EXPELLED?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
DON’T BE SILLY.
WHAT DO I GET OUT OF YOU
BEING EXPELLED?
THAT DOESN’T BENEFIT ME.
I JUST WANT TO IMPROVE
MY OVERALL SCHOOL EXPERIENCE.
AND I PLAN TO DO THAT
BY TURNING YOU INTO MY LOYAL,
OBEDIENT LITTLE DOG...
A CLEVER DOG WHO KNOWS THE ONLY
WAY TO SAVE HIS OWN HIDE
IS BY GIVING ME
BURST POINTS DAILY.
( gasping )
Chiyuri: I WON’T
LET YOU DO THAT!
( grunts softly )
HARU WENT INTO THE GIRL’S
SHOWER ROOM
BECAUSE I ASKED HIM TO.
AND IF HE CHOOSES
TO MAKE THAT VIDEO PUBLIC,
THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT I’LL SAY.
I ASKED HIM THERE
BECAUSE I SPRAINED
MY ANKLE SO BADLY,
I COULDN’T WALK ON MY OWN.
CHIYU.
NICELY DONE.
I ADMIT I’M RATHER IMPRESSED,
KURASHIMA SENPAI.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU CONSIDER
THAT YOU’RE A BRAND-NEW
BURST-LINKER.
STOP TRYING
TO BE THE TOUGH GUY!
YOUR LITTLE ACT
IS OVER, OKAY?
THAT VIDEO WON’T
BE OF ANY USE NOW.
YEAH. I’M NOT
SO SURE ABOUT THAT.
LET’S PICTURE THIS:
RIGHT ABOUT NOW,
SOMEONE’S GONNA
FIND ANOTHER CAMERA
JUST LIKE THIS ONE
HIDDEN IN THE GIRLS’
SHOWER ROOM.
WHAT DO YOU
THINK HAPPENS NEXT?
IT’LL CAUSE A HUGE FUSS
AND A BIG SEARCH
FOR THE CULPRIT.
NOW, IF I UPLOADED THIS VIDEO
HERE ONTO THE LOCAL NET,
TELL ME, KURASHIMA SENPAI,
WOULD YOUR COVER-UP STILL
BE ENOUGH TO SAVE YOUR FRIEND?
( gasps )
YOU’D GO THAT FAR?
SERIOUSLY?
( bell ringing )
Man: WE HAVE AN URGENT MESSAGE
FROM THE UMESATO JUNIOR HIGH
ADMINISTRATION.
EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY,
ALL STUDENTS ARE FORBIDDEN
FROM ENTERING THE AREA
INDICATED HERE ON THE MAP.
WELL NOW, IT SEEMS THEY
FOUND THE CAMERA AT LAST.
BUT THAT’S TO BE EXPECTED
SINCE I SET THE RECORD LIGHT
TO START BLINKING
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
ARE YOU TOTALLY WHACKED?
GOING TO ALL THIS TROUBLE
JUST TO GET AHEAD IN SOME GAME?
GET REAL!
THERE’S A QUESTION
THAT I’D LIKE TO ASK YOU,
SENPAI.
DO YOU STILL HONESTLY
THINK THAT WAY?
( gasps )
THAT BRAIN BURST
IS JUST A GAME?
( gasps )
( whimpering )
( groans )
AND DON’T EVER TALK TO ME
LIKE THAT AGAIN.
IT’S RUDE.
AFTER ALL,
YOU HAVE TO OBEY ME, TOO.
ISN’T THAT RIGHT?
( gasps )
I’VE GOT BIG PLANS FOR YOU.
YOU’LL BE MY
SPECIAL PET, OKAY?
( whimpering )
EVERY SINGLE TIME
I DUEL IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD,
YOU’LL BE THERE TO SERVE ME.
IT’S ALL RIGHT.
DON’T GET TOO UPSET.
I DON’T INTEND TO MAKE YOU
DO SOMETHING AGAINST YOUR WILL
IN THE REAL WORLD.
OR PERHAPS I SHOULD
SAY NOT RIGHT NOW.
( whimpering )
( laughing )
YOU...SON OF A...
( panting )
NO ONE SAID YOU COULD MOVE.
I TOLD YOU, DIDN’T I?
GAME OVER.
YOU’RE DONE.
NOW JUST SIT THERE
AND BE A GOOD LITTLE DOGGIE,
ALL RIGHT?
SORRY. I MEAN "SENPAI."
( whimpering )
( squeals )
( laughing )
( whimpering )
NOMI!!!
( no audible dialogue )
( gasps )
Both: PHYSICAL BURST.
( thinking )
I SHOULDN’T BE DOING THIS...
BUT...I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I CAN’T JUST STAND THERE
AND LET THIS NOMI CREEP
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
IT’S ONE THING
TO COME AFTER ME.
BUT NOT CHIYU!
DAMN IT.
HARU!
( blow landing )
( grunting )
OH, WOW, YOU REALLY
DO SUCK AT THIS, SENPAI.
I GOTTA SAY IT SHOULD
HAVE BEEN PRETTY OBVIOUS
WHEN YOU’RE FIGHTING
IN A PHYSICALLY
ACCELERATED STATE,
IT’S ALL ABOUT USING
ANTICIPATION AND FEINTS.
( whimpering )
I DON’T THINK I EVEN NEEDED
TO USE THAT COMMAND WITH YOU.
I JUST WASTED FIVE
WHOLE POINTS.
( groaning )
( laughing )
WE STILL HAVE THREE MINUTES
BEFORE CLASS STARTS UP AGAIN.
THAT SHOULD BE PLENTY OF TIME.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED THE TWO
OF US TO HAVE A DUEL?
THEN WHY DON’T WE
GO AHEAD AND MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
( groaning loudly )
( metal clicking )
( chuckling )
BURST LINK.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( song ends )
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE: DESTRUCTION.
HARUYUKI
PREPARES FOR HIS FIGHT.
BUT NOMI’S DARK POWERS
THREATEN TO DESTROY EVERYTHING.