♪
[AKANE] Everyone who
lives here has no choice
but to love
everything about me.
That's why you and
I are friends, Rikka.
[RIKKA] Are you saying I was
born already as your friend?
[AKANE]
That's right.
You were made to be my friend
when you were made by my kaiju.
There's no way. I'm alive
because my parents had me.
[YUTA] Yeah. I want
to think that too.
This city and everyone who lives
here was born by Akane's kaiju.
And if you go beyond
the city, nothing exists.
[UTSUMI] What about
when we went rafting?
[YUTA] She made the spot up
for us. That whole area.
Okay, but. I've got
relatives in Inagi.
And for my third year of middle
school, we went to Kyoto.
[gasps] But what if my entire
past was invented for me?
Considering what's
been going on,
I can't trust in my
own memories anymore.
Like how we never noticed
the kaiju all over the city
until Hibiki brought them up.
[GRIDMAN] Akane Shinjo...
is the god of this city?
[FURUMA] Argh, shoot! It's gone.
Is it mixed in with your stuff?
[AKANE]
I told you, no.
[MARUSAN]
What are you looking for?
I wish we were in the festival.
There's always next year.
But aren't you going
to pick science
for next year's
courses, Tonkawa?
[KENA] But we'll be
in different classes!
[TONKAWA] We can just
participate as a group.
[AKANE] What are those
girls doing here?
[MUKO]
What can five people even do?
Yeah, we definitely
need more to join.
Hm? Hey. You want
in with us, Akane?
[gasps]
[victims murmuring]
[AKANE gasps]
[AKANE]
A dream? But I saw...
[ALEXIS] Real humans
don't actually sleep.
More importantly, hurry up and
finish your latest masterpiece.
Could you remind me why
I have to make kaiju again?
[UTSUMI]
You're saying Akane Shinjo
made everything in this city,
and we've got no choice
but to live here?
--[smacking]
--[UTSUMI yelps]
You think whining about it
is going to solve anything?
No, but...
[YUTA]
Let's go...
...over to Shinjo's place.
I agree.
Just walk straight over?
[YUTA]
Mm-hm. Right up to the door.
We don't know what danger might
be waiting for us inside.
If Shinjo really is being used
by an alien, we have to go.
[RIKKA exhles]
[doorbell chimes]
Maybe she's not home.
[MAX]
Let's check.
[RIKKA]
Uh-hey!
Seriously?
[YUTA]
Uh...
[BOTH gasp]
[UTSUMI] What in the...?
What is this place?
She.. She must've fled.
[YUTA]
But to where?
Why isn't anything going
the way I planned it?
Even though I know
Gridman's true identity.
I wonder.
What took him so long to show
up during the rafting trip?
[TATSUMI]
Aren't midterms next week?
[HAYAKAWA] And the
regionals too. I'm so screwed.
[FURUMA]
You think she's okay?
Dunno, she hasn't shown
up for school in a week.
Hey! Who knows what's
wrong with Akane?
[TEACHER] I guess her
cold is pretty severe.
So, all of you,
try to stay healthy.
Alright, let's get started.
[ONDA]
Stand!
[chairs clattering]
[ONDA]
Attention! Bow!
[chairs clattering]
[YUTA] Yet another
day without a kaiju.
It's a good thing.
It's bad, I'm sure of it.
How's it bad?
Because Akane
Shinjo's disappeared.
So what happens to us?
I don't know, but nothing
has gone wrong so far.
[UTSUMI] Not yet, anyway.
But Shinjo created this world.
And if she's not around,
everything, including us,
could just vanish for good.
[YUTA] Aren't you
overthinking it a bit?
[YUTA]
Huh? Utsumi?
And that was it.
That explains why he didn't
come by after school.
[YUTA] He probably doesn't
want to talk about it.
[RIKKA gasps]
[BORR] It's possible the
kaiju beyond the fog
are responsible for how
everybody keeps resetting.
The only ones who don't
seem to be affected by it
are Gridman and us.
It, it isn't a fog.
If memories are
being tampered with,
it's a poisonous nerve gas.
[GRIDMAN]
A poison smoke kaiju.
Then does that mean Shinjo's the
reason I lost my memories too?
I don't know. If she could
do something like that,
wouldn't it be easy for
her to defeat Gridman?
[GRIDMAN] We came to the world
that Akane Shinjo created.
We arrived here in
an incomplete state,
and then met Yuta.
[YUTA] At that point,
I'd already lost my memories.
Ugh. I don't understand
any of this.
There're just too
many mysteries.
For example,
where did Akane go?
[MAX] Seeing as how
we can combine into
Full Powered Gridman,
it's likely we were
originally one entity.
[CALIBUR] M-Meaning we were
separate before coming here?
[VIT] I think it's more like we
were separated from each other.
[BORR]
By who? Oh...
[GRIDMAN]
Alexis Kerib.
[YUTA]
I think...
...the danger Gridman
mentioned is still around.
[ALEXIS] Akane, what is
the matter with you?
[ALEXIS] Perhaps you're
experiencing a slump?
[ALEXIS] Oh you're finished?
You're fine with this one?
[ANNOUNCER]
I repeat.
There's a special broadcast
meeting after school.
Members must come
to the broadcast room.
Is everything okay, Utsumi?
Huh? With what?
Well, you weren't at
the shop yesterday.
Yeah, I was studying.
Huh?
For mid-term exams. There's no
telling when a kaiju's gonna
show up, but our test
dates are set in stone.
You got a point.
[UTSUMI] Right? Even if this
is Akane Shinjo's world.
As long as we're living here,
there's certain things
we still gotta do.
Our lives are about more
than just fighting kaiju.
Yeah, I understand that, but...
[UTSUMI] If it ain't broke,
don't fix it. You know?
[RIKKA]
What's with that?
I guess he's feeling better
cause it's a brand new week.
[GRIDMAN]
I see.
[YUTA] Well, I'm just
glad he's fine now.
[YUTA] I wonder why Shinjo
created this city
in the first place.
[GRIDMAN] Because it's somewhere
Akane Shinjo could live easily.
She sought out tranquility.
[YUTA] For a world she
made to live easy in,
she sure seems suffocated by it.
Speaking of which, don't the
gods have a world of their own?
Maybe she escaped from it to
come here for some reason.
That seems kinda weak
for her in my opinion.
[RIKKA]
It's not that she's weak.
I would call Akane sensitive.
I hope there's no
kaiju tomorrow either.
Me too.
[CALIBUR grunts]
[ANTI grunts]
[ANTI exhales]
[CALIBUR] You're after
Gridman, aren't you?
[ANTI]
That's right.
[CALIBUR]
You lose and keep living.
Eating and bathing,
despite being a kaiju.
[ANTI] If I don't stay alive,
I can't beat Gridman.
And after you
defeat him, then what?
[gasps]
I can tell. Your face says
you've never thought about it.
Someone who blurs the line
between kaiju and human
will never win.
But I...! I live only
to crush Gridman!
That's everything to me!
[KAIJU A roars]
[CALIBUR]
Hm.
[YUTA] Yeah. I felt
it over here too.
[RIKKA]
There goes our break.
[UTSUMI] Another kaiju?
So that means...
Get out of here, guys!
A kaiju's coming this way!
A kaiju?
[HASS] The three of them
seem to be having fun.
[NAMIKO]
Huh?
[YUTA] I knew it! Shinjo must
be somewhere in the city!
--[door clatters]
--[Group] Hm?
We're all here.
There's no time to waste!
[ALL] Hyperlink Combine.
Full Powered Gridman!
[KAIJU A roars]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[roaring]
[GRIDMAN grunting]
[GRIDMAN]
Breast Spark!
[KAIJU A groans]
[VIT]
Uh, that was quick.
[BORR]
Pathetic. What gives?
[MAX] Stay alert!
The fight isn't over yet!
[GRIDMAN gasps]
[ANTI grunts]
[VIT]
So that's how it is?
[ANTI]
You guessed it!
Not even a scratch?
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[ANTI shouts]
[BORR] You don't know
when to quit, do you?
Don't you ever get
sick of losing?
[ANTI grunts]
I'll keep on fighting,
until I finally crush Gridman!
[BOTH grunting]
[GRIDMAN]
Full Power Charge!
Hell yeah! Let's see if a
copycat like you can win now!
[ANTI grunting]
Why... Why won't you kill me?
Answer me!
[UTSUMI] That kaiju
was weird. Don't you think?
The corpse is still there.
[MAX]
You held back the final blow.
[GRIDMAN]
No. I defeated it.
Wrong one. We meant
the other kaiju.
You know, the annoying guy
who always gets in our way.
[GRIDMAN]
Well, that's...
It's because he's not like the
others we've fought before.
I'm not following.
[CALIBUR] He studied humans.
And got too close to them.
He's a living being
with a heart now.
[MAX] Gridman won't steal
the lives of the living.
But aren't the kaiju
technically living too?
[GRIDMAN] Kaiju are like
the malice of Akane Shinjo,
and thus don't have lives.
Yeah, but... this one was born
with a hatred for Gridman
from the very beginning.
[GRIDMAN] He must have become
a living being from a kaiju.
[AKANE]
Looks like we lost again.
Do Kaiju only exist for the
sake of being defeated?
[AKANE] Long time no see.
Still hanging in there?
[AKANE]
You remember this place?
I treated you to a meal here
back when you first
defeated Gridman.
[ANTI] Why? Why give
life to a kaiju like me?
[AKANE]
You're not a kaiju anymore.
[ANTI]
Why not?
[AKANE] Because kaiju can't
read people's feelings.
You came looking
for me, didn't you?
The thing is, kaiju don't go
out of their way for people.
They ruin people's
lives just by existing.
That's a kaiju.
And I don't like kaiju
that resemble people.
Your eyes. You have
eyes like a person.
[ANTI]
And your eyes are.
[AKANE]
Don't look. Go somewhere.
Wherever you like.
[AKANE] I knew you
were a failed creation.
[ALEXIS] Oh. Looks like there
was another hiding inside.
Is this okay?
[AKANE]
[KAIJU B laughs]
[gasps]
Everyone in my city is dead?
[ALEXIS]
Those kaiju were custodians.
They can easily be replaced.
[ALEXIS chuckles]
[beeping]
[YUTA gasps]
[YUTA]
What's going on?
[BORR]
Dunno,
but another kaiju came out
of the earlier one's corpse.
[MAX] It appears to have
attacked the kaiju
beyond the fog.
[VIT] I suppose that's why
it's starting to clear up.
[UTSUMI]
Those scenery kaiju are dead?
[CALIBUR] Yeah, I confirmed
their bodies.
[YUTA]
Gridman. Let's go!
[GRIDMAN] Right! We'll crush
it with full power!
[YUTA]
Access Flash!
[ALL]
Access Code...!
[ALL] Hyperlink Combine.
Full Powered Gridman!
[KAIJU B roars]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[BORR]
Hey, what's your problem?
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[BORR]
You'll pay for that!
[KAIJU B laughs]
[GRIDMAN grunting]
It's too strong for them.
[UTSUMI gasps]
[MAX] This kaiju's unlike
any we've fought before!
I can't read its movements!
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[KAIJU B laughs]
[UTSUMI gasps]
[UTSUMI]
Crap!
What is that thing?!
[MAX] This is bad.
It's going after Gridman!
[GRIDMAN groans]
[YUTA screams]
He's in trouble. What do we do?
Just run, Hibiki!
[ANTI shouts]
It's him!
[MAX]
He helped Gridman?
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[GRIDMAN]
It's you.
[KAIJU B shouts]
[ANTI yells]
[ANTI shouts]
[KAIJU B grunts]
[ANTI yells]
[GRIDMAN]
Why are you fighting for me?
[AKANE] Go somewhere.
Wherever you like.
I know there has to be a
reason I was given life.
And I'll find it.
[ANTI]
I... I was born to crush you!
And I live on to crush you!
[KAIJU B laughs]
[ANTI grunts] In order to
do that. I will... fight...
...together with you!
[ALL gasp]
[MAX]
He copied Gridman!
[VIT]
So now there are two?
[BORR]
It's a fake.
[CALIBUR] N-No. This one...
is the real deal.
[ANTI shouts]
[KAIJU B, ANTI grunting]
[ANTI] I feel it. This is
Akane Shinjo's heart itself!
[AKANE] Because kaiju can't
read people's feelings.
[ANTI gasps]
[ANTI]
But I can read her heart.
In that case...!
[ANTI yells]
He's got 'em!
[ANTI] I can see right
through you, Akane Shinjo!
[KAIJU B groans]
[MAX]
A knight who protected Gridman.
[YUTA]
Gridknight.
So that explains it.
[ALL gasp]
Akane?
I was totally convinced
Hibiki was Gridman.
But I was a little off.
This is how you've
been transforming.
I had no idea. To think,
you needed this old computer.
Wait, are you saying, even gods
don't know everything?
Of course. Be honest, Utsumi.
Do you remember every single
thing you've ever thrown away?
This shop is a dumping ground
for junk people
don't need anymore.
Open your eyes, Shinjo.
Don't you realize whoever that
alien is, he's using you? So--
I wanted to try talking
to Gridman myself.
♪