[gasps, grunts]
[YUTA breathes heavily]
[AKANE]
I... stabbed him.
[All gasp]
[RIKKA]
Hibiki!
[gasps]
[MAX]
Hang in there, Yuta!
[BORR]
C'mon, hey!
Sorry, but this had to happen.
[AKANE] I know, I'm so rotten.
But there isn't any other way!
[clattering]
[RIKKA]
Akane!
What in the world
is all the commotion?
Huh? What happened?
Call an ambulance, now!
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Uh...
Hurry up!
Uh. Right.
[RIKKA'S MOM gasps] What the--?
The phone's not working.
[CALIBUR]
Neither is my cell.
[UTSUMI gasps]
Hibiki...
[UTSUMI]
Yuta. Hey, c'mon.
You're gonna be okay,
aren't you?
Hey, Yuta!
[YUTA]
Grid...man.
♪
[BORR]
Pull it more that way.
[CALIBUR]
Hm?
[BORR]
Yeah, so it's not caught.
[MAX]
I'll close it.
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Alright, I'm going!
[ALL]
We're ready.
[UTSUMI]
This morning, is like no other.
[BORR] Every other time
a kaiju attacked,
it all reset by morning.
So what's gonna happen now?
[CALIBUR]
H-His treatment is done.
[UTSUMI]
Yuta.
[MAX] Fortunately,
his vitals were missed.
His life is not in any danger.
[RIKKA]
I see.
[UTSUMI sighs] Thank goodness.
Oh man, thank goodness.
I tried over and over again to
get a hold of Hibiki's parents,
but It's as if none of
the phones will connect.
N-No. It's not just the phones.
Looks like the net's down too.
[MAX] It seems every form of
communication in the city
is out of order.
[UTSUMI] I wonder if it's
because those scenery-like
kaiju all died.
[MAX] If those kaiju
maintained the whole city,
then the city and everyone's
memories won't be reset.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] Dr. Amaji
from Internal Medicine...
[MAN A]
Sorry, coming through.
[RIKKA'S MOM grunts]
Why don't you sit?
I'm going to head to school.
[VIT sighs]
I guess students still
have to attend classes
even during times like this?
I'm just going to
check things out.
[DISASTER SHELTER
ATTENDANTS chattering]
[RIKKA] Looks like I'll
have to search for Akane.
Even if she had her reasons,
what she did is unforgivable.
[NAMIKO, HASS]
Hey! Rikka!
[NAMIKO]
What a relief!
I thought I'd never
see you again!
[RIKKA]
Don't go killing me off now.
[RIKKA] So, hey. There's no
way we can really know, but,
lots of people have died up
till now, don't you think?
[NAMIKO]
Huh?
[HASS]
Up till now?
[RIKKA] Uh, well. Like in
accidents or disasters.
[HASS]
Yeah, that's a given.
Still, I never would've imagined
that a kaiju would show up here.
Kinda reminds me of
practice disaster drills.
It's all so unbelievable.
Yeah, but, hey. On the
plus side, those big guys
appeared out of nowhere
and beat the thing for us!
[HASS]
Yeah!
[NAMIKO]
Speaking of which.
How the heck did you know a
kaiju would come yesterday?
[HASS]
Spill it.
[RIKKA]
Huh? Oh I, uh...
[NAMIKO, HASS]
Hmm...?
[ALEXIS] Akane. I'd like to
discuss the next kaiju with you.
There won't be a next one.
I don't need them anymore.
[ALEXIS]
And why's that?
[AKANE]
Because Hibiki is...
Because I brought
down Gridman already.
[ALEXIS sighs]
But the trouble is...
It seems that Anti has become
the next Gridman in line.
There's still a need
for kaiju after all.
Your kaiju, that is.
[AKANE]
I can't make kaiju anymore.
[ALEXIS sighs]
Is that so?
[ALEXIS] So be it.
I'll use what's available.
[KAIJU roaring]
[HASS]
Whoa, some more kaiju appeared!
[NAMIKO]
It's a bunch of 'em!
[RIKKA]
Sorry, I've gotta go!
[NAMIKO] That girl. You know
she's hiding something.
[HASS] Maybe, but you shouldn't
just assume that's a bad thing.
If there's something
she's not telling us,
that means Rikka thinks
it's better left unsaid.
You sure have a way of
seeing things, Hass.
[HASS]
That's because I'm her friend.
[NAMIKO]
Because of that?
[HASS]
Yup.
I thought you'd already be gone.
They're saying
they can't do it.
Go out and fight, I mean.
[RIKKA gasps]
The power we have exists
only because of Gridman.
Until Yuta wakes up,
Gridman won't.
[footsteps]
[ANTI] You choose to do nothing,
thinking nothing can be done.
[RIKKA]
Anti?
Uh, you know him?
[MAX]
What do you want?
[UTSUMI gasps]
You all know him? Who is this?
He's a kaiju that goes around
pretending to be human.
[RIKKA, UTSUMI]
Huh?
The one that is always
getting in our way!
Seriously?
He's a kaiju?
Not anymore.
I'm no longer a kaiju.
Oh wow, is that right?
The thing is, no matter what,
I won't accept you as Gridman.
[RIKKA'S MOM grunts]
Is it true? Are you that
copycat kaiju we keep seeing?
Who the hell are you?
A normal person.
One of the many you
crush under your feet.
I represent the people.
Whatever. If I watch
my step, I can't fight.
[gasps]
It must be my lucky day getting
to meet a kaiju in person.
Lemme guess, you've come
to apologize to us?
What's apologize mean?
[UTSUMI gasps]
Want me to show you?
Cut it out! This is a hospital.
There are enough
injured here already.
[UTSUMI] When kaiju run rampant,
a lot of people become victims.
But... I...
To think I enjoyed seeing
Gridman fight them.
[UTSUMI]
I'm despicable.
Nothing's gonna change the
fact that you're a kaiju.
And because of you,
countless people have died.
But, right now, there's no one
else around we can rely on.
That is exactly what
I came here for.
[ALL gasp]
Paying my debts.
[ANTI] I was taught
that's good manners.
That's so polite.
--[CALIBUR laughs]
--[BORR] Whoa, what the hell?
I've never seen
him laugh before.
It's gross.
I think it's sort of cute.
Alright, Gridknight.
We request your assistance.
Who is this Gridknight?
From now on, it's the
new name... of your new form.
Is it?
Wait up! Where is
Akane right now?
[KAIJU roaring]
[ANTI, KAIJU grunting]
[ANTI]
Grid... Knight... Circular!
[KAIJU groan]
[roars]
[ANTI shouts]
[KAIJU C groans]
[KAIJU A groans]
Okay, he's pretty good.
But there's just too many
enemies for him to handle.
Alright. So what
would happen now
if this were actually a
part of the Ultra series?
What the heck?
What's even the
point of fighting?
[FEMALE NURSE] Kanesue?
Is Yuichiro Kanesue here?
[MAX] I wonder.
Why won't Yuta wake up?
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Hypovolemic shock maybe?
Though, the doctor was saying
it's absurd for that to cause
a coma, so I don't know.
[BORR] Hmm. It might
be absurd, but Yuta is--
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Hm? Something wrong?
Is that how it is?
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Hm?
We need you to come with us.
Where are we going?
[footsteps]
Huh? What the--?
There they go.
[KAIJU roar]
[VIT] Up until now, Junk only
worked when Yuta was there.
[BORR] If Junk and Yuta
are connected somehow,
then Yuta should wake
up if we fix Junk again.
[MAX]
Yuta and Junk are connected.
So Junk and Gridman
being connected means...
[CALIBUR] ...that Gridman
and Yuta are probably...
[KAIJU groan]
[ANTI]
Grid... Knight... Storm!
[CALIBUR]
Hmm...
[VIT grunts]
[BORR]
Let's see.
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Hm?
[BORR]
Oh! Look what I found!
That's an Optional 3-D Graphic
Animation Board, isn't it?
Sixteen million, seven hundred
seventy-seven thousand
two hundred-sixteen colors.
I guess we're lucky this
place is a thrift store.
It was thrown in the trash.
The trash? You think
it still works?
[CALIBUR]
We'll know in a moment.
[RIKKA'S MOM] I hate to
break it to you guys,
but that still counts as
the shop's property.
That's why we had
you come with us.
Cause it's something that
belongs to the shop.
We'll take care of it.
[RIKKA'S MOM sighs]
If you want it that badly,
I guess you can just have it.
You did buy it once.
Thank you.
We'll take it in due time.
But right now, it's needed here.
[AKANE] What's wrong with
a dream? Let's keep it going.
Just like this.
[RIKKA gasps]
I... have to go.
Take care of Hibiki!
[UTSUMI scoffs]
It's just me. Everyone has
things they must do.
But all I can do
is stay with Yuta.
[YUTA]
Huh...? Wait, Gridman?
Where is this?
[GRIDMAN]
This, Yuta, is inside you.
[YUTA]
What exactly are you doing
inside of me, Gridman?
[GRIDMAN]
Why is Yuta inside of me ?
Because you are me.
Then Gridman is me?
I shouldn't remember anything.
It's not that I'm Yuta, but
Gridman dwelling inside of Yuta.
Hold on. Why did you
dwell inside Yuta?
[GRIDMAN] In Akane
Shinjo's world, he alone--
There. That should about do it.
[YUTA grunts]
Huh?
You're awake!
[ANTI pants]
Is that the last of 'em?
[ANTI grunts]
[ANTI shouts]
[KAIJU D grunts]
[ANTI grunts]
[KAIJU D roars]
[KAIJU E growls]
[YUTA] Utsumi, I'm sorry.
I didn't have amnesia after all.
I think I never had
memories to begin with.
[UTSUMI gasps]
What do you mean?
[YUTA] I... I am Gridman
dwelling inside Yuta.
Huh?
Then I... This whole time,
I was actually with Gridman
who thought he was Yuta?
[YUTA] Yeah. Which is why the
real Yuta is still fast asleep.
And will be until I leave.
But before that, there's
something I must do here still.
[UTSUMI] Still? You mean
keep using Yuta?
What else is going to
happen to his body?
Yuta was... Yuta was
stabbed by Akane Shinjo!
[ANTI yells]
[YUTA] Yes. Shinjo had
no choice but to stab me.
She was driven so far into a
corner by the same world
she made, that it was
the only option for her.
Which is why,
There's something I must do.
Something that only I can do.
[UTSUMI grunts]
Stop it, Gridman!
You're going to kill Yuta!
Sorry, Utsumi. But I
have to be going now.
You're not acting
like yourself at all.
That may be so, but...
[YUTA, GRIDMAN]
I am a Hyper Agent.
I am called Gridman.
[gasps]
In the end...
I never did anything.
[ALEXIS]
Very well done, Anti.
However, it's about
time to end this.
[KAIJU F growls]
[YUTA pants]
He's here?
[MAX] Yuta. I take it
you're Gridman now?
[YUTA, GRIDMAN]
That's right.
Access... Flash!
[MAX]
Let's go too!
[VIT]
Uh...
[BORR] I'm guessing
you saw all of that.
Don't mind me.
If you have to go, go.
[MAX]
Well, then.
[ALL]
Access code...
[gasps]
[chuckles]
See you soon.
Hey, look up there!
Something's flying!
[HASS]
Nice colors.
[KAIJU F growls]
[ANTI gasps]
[ANTI]
You're here!
[GRIDMAN ] Sorry to make
you wait, Gridknight.
[ANTI]
You're late, Gridman.
[GRIDMAN shouts]
[CALIBUR]
Take ahold of me.
[ANTI]
Gridknight Calibur!
[KAIJU roaring]
[BORR]
Twin Buster...
[GRIDMAN]
...Grid...
[GRIDMAN, BORR]
...Beam!
[roars]
[ANTI]
Knight...
[CALIBUR]
...Calibur...
[ANTI, CALIBUR]
...End!
What did you come for?
I've been looking all
over for you, Akane.
[AKANE]
'Cause of what I did to Hibiki?
You do know if you had
just killed me sooner,
none of this would
have happened.
Don't say that. Why is that
all you ever think about?
I can't help it.
[RIKKA]
Hibiki?
He's still alive?
But how? I stabbed him though.
[RIKKA gasps]
[AKANE]
Don't follow me.
[RIKKA gaps]
I bet you think
I'm a stupid god
without any control
over her world!
Akane...
Just go away and join
your friends already!
It's not like this
even involves you!
How does it not involve me?
How could you even
say that? I...
Unlike you,
I'm not a god, but,
I still think of
you as a friend.
[AKANE]
Yeah, but that's...
You only think that because
I set you up that way.
I made you believe
we were friends!
You and I are friends, Akane.
I don't need any other reason
to be born than that.
[RIKKA] What do you
think of me, Akane?
[AKANE]
I...
[ALEXIS] Sorry to end
this pointless chat,
but I must interrupt.
It's the alien.
[ALEXIS] Hurry it up, Akane.
You're needed after all.
[AKANE] I told you,
I can't make kaiju anymore.
[ALEXIS] Unfortunately, I think
you misunderstand me.
I'm fine with you becoming
a kaiju yourself.
[gasps]
[ALEXIS]
Instance Abreaction!
♪