♪
[MAN A]
Yes. Yes, that's right.
I think it'll be done shortly.
Exactly.
Listen. You think you could
wait a little bit longer?
[AKANE hums]
[YUTA groans]
[AKANE humming]
[AKANE continues humming]
Oh. You're awake.
Good morning. If it is.
I started to worry about you
when I couldn't get
you to wake up.
[YUTA]
Um...
[AKANE]
Hm?
[YUTA]
Who are you?
Are you alright?
Did you hit your head?
Do you know who you are?
[AKANE gasps]
You've got amnesia!
[YUTA grunts]
[YUTA gasps]
[YUTA]
Hm... Huh?
You there. What're you doing?
Huh? Uh. I'm sorry, I'll go!
Ugh! So this is where
you ran off to!
Yuta, you shouldn't be
wandering around alone
while you have amnesia!
Yuta... Wait, is that my name?
Yup. Yuta Hibiki.
Mama. I'm going to take
him to the hospital.
[YUTA]
The mist sure is thick.
[AKANE]
Is it?
[YUTA]
Huh?
What is this?
Something you always wear.
It's my wristwatch.
[AKANE]
So, how'd it go?
A lot of it went
over my head but,
they said I'd be back
to normal before long.
Oh yeah? That's awesome news!
[YUTA chuckles]
Well, guess I better head
on home. Thanks for everything.
Sure. But do you
know where you live?
[YUTA]
Uh...!
[AKANE]
I'll take you there.
[YUTA] So, hey. Why was I
sleeping over at your house?
You were coming
home from school.
Then you collapsed
and slept at my place.
What do you mean?
Uh, do we have a history?
Like, uh... are we friends?
Well, actually, you and I
are boyfriend and girlfriend.
Huh?! Oh, well that's
good to know.
You don't remember, do you?
Nope. Nothing.
But, well, I can't help but
feel I lucked out a bit.
That's cruel! How could
you say that?
This guy, unbelievable.
[YUTA gasps]
Wait!
[YUTA] Huh? Hey!
I didn't mean it! Really!
[AKANE]
Well, this is where you live.
[YUTA]
Right. Thank you.
[AKANE]
I'll be going home then.
[YUTA]
Oh, okay. See you later.
--[AKANE] Boo.
--[YUTA gasps]
[AKANE giggles]
What, no kiss or anything?
[YUTA gasps]
[AKANE] Got you!
I'll see you tomorrow!
I think my heart stopped.
[YUTA]
I'm home.
It's dark.
[YUTA]
Hm?
[YUTA] Losing my memory
might not be so bad.
[RIKKA] Excuse me? I'm not
feeling very well today.
[AKANE]
Nobody's here.
You skipping class too?
Your name's Shinjo, right?
[AKANE]
Just call me Akane.
Those club introductions were
taking forever to get through.
You thinking of joining one?
Yeah, I'm leaning towards no.
Back in middle school we
were forced to sign up,
but now that I have a choice,
I'd rather just go home.
I totally agree,
no club for me either.
So where did you go
to middle school?
I'm from Matsugasaki.
My secret.
[RIKKA]
What the heck?
And here I was thinking you
took everything seriously.
[AKANE giggling]
Me? Please.
[AKANE]
But if you're curious for real,
I actually moved to the
area just this spring.
[RIKKA gasps]
You did?
[AKANE]
As a matter of fact,
my house is right
next door to yours.
Haven't you noticed?
[RIKKA]
You're kidding me!
Wow, incredible! I mean,
what a huge coincidence!
Yup, a huge coincidence.
[AKANE]
Utsumi, right?
[UTSUMI]
Huh? Sh-Shinjo?
How come you're
dressed up all fancy?
Oh. I was at a relative's
memorial service.
So, what are you reading?
Well, that one is--
[AKANE]
Spaceship, huh?
Yeah.
I just happened to pick it up
completely at random, honest.
[AKANE]
Oh, it's Red King.
Huh?
[AKANE]
Without a doubt,
his third model is best
out of all of them.
Whoa. Wait, Shinjo.
You're into kaiju?
[AKANE]
Hm?  I sure am.
There's no way!
Here, lemme see that.
Tell me what this one is called.
What? Are you talking
about Yadokarin?
[gasps]
Then what about over here?
Oh, it'll come to me...
Female Majaba!
That's Chaos Jirak.
Abnu Ogma, I think?
Of course I know this one!
It's Gomora! With uh...
Reionic Burst!
You're amazing!
[AKANE]
Hm?
[UTSUMI] No, I mean...
Check it out!
I wish I had bought this
when they were available.
[AKANE]
Ultra Mech Selection mark two?
I saw it at Nakano
the other day.
Are you serious?
[AKANE]
Mm-hm!
[UTSUMI gasps]
Hey! Let's go there together!
...Meaning you and me?
[RIKKA]
Hello, please excuse me.
My parents aren't around,
so don't worry about it.
They're not here?
No, they're never
around, actually.
They aren't? I'm sorry.
Didn't I just tell
you not to worry?
Besides, I have someone
who takes care of me.
I wonder if they're home.
Are you here, Alexis?
A foreigner?
[ALEXIS] Did you call
for me, Miss Akane?
[RIKKA gasps]
What the...?
May I introduce you
to Alexis Kerib.
[ALEXIS]
Salutations.
Is he an alien?
And where's all that
smoke coming from?
[ALEXIS]
Hm?
[AKANE giggles]
It's cosplay, Rikka!
He really went all out.
[AKANE] If that smoke was real,
he'd have a big problem!
Yeah. You kinda
got a point there.
[ALEXIS] I apologize
for surprising you.
It's cool. I don't know
what I was thinking.
Sorry about that.
[AKANE chuckles]
Rikka, you're the absolute best!
Always a hundred percent honest.
[RIKKA]
Huh?
[UTSUMI cheers] At long last,
it's finally mine! All mine!
This is a dream come true!
[AKANE]
Glad we came?
Yeah! I owe you
big time, Shinjo!
This is the only decent
Space Mammy in existence!
Hey. Do you happen to know how
long this series was out for?
Um, I'm not sure. But I'm
pretty certain there were some
released from Super GUTS.
[MALE ANNOUNCER A]
Classic Leader. Classic Leader,
to the third floor
trade counter, please.
[UTSUMI gasps]
It looks like they
made four sets total.
Yeah...
Whatta shame the Hexa Wing
wasn't a part of it, huh?
♪
[AKANE] That's exactly how
things should have been.
Because they,
like everybody else,
were made so they would like me.
[ALEXIS] I'm glad to
see it's going so well.
[AKANE]
You really think so?
[ALEXIS]
Of course. I'm impressed.
The only person who can
create such a magnificent kaiju,
is you.
What's with this?
How come Gridman
isn't appearing?
[BORR]
Utsumi! Hey! Wake up!
What the heck? It's useless.
Nothing can wake them up.
Th-That kaiju has
to be the reason.
Nothing can touch it.
However, it's not
causing damage, either.
Only those three
are fast asleep.
Think they're having
a good dream?
[MAX]
A dream.
[inaudible]
[YUTA gasps]
[AKANE]
What're you doing?
Let's hurry up!
Right.
Wh-What do you want?
Oh, don't you even think about
coming in here all soaking wet!
Invest in a damn umbrella!
[ANTI]
Bring out Gridman!
Crushing him is the only
thing that matters to me!
Unfortunately, Gridman's out
on vacation today.
Don't screw with me!
It's the truth. As long as that
kaiju out there is undefeated,
Gridman won't appear.
[ANTI]
All right then.
[ANTI grunts]
[ANTI shouts]
That guy's got a one
track mind, doesn't he?
[ANTI yells]
[AKANE]
Huh? What's that about?
[ALEXIS]
Strange.
I wonder if Anti changed his
mind and likes Gridman now.
[AKANE] That's not what
I was talking about.
Didn't you deal with him?
[ALEXIS] Uh, sorry.
He got away from me.
But wouldn't it be
nice if Gridman
were to disappear
for good?
Yeah.
[YUTA]
Akane... Akane...
Akane?
[AKANE gasps]
Everything okay?
[AKANE] Oh, yeah.
Just spaced out for a second.
I like walking around in
cemeteries during the summer.
During the summer?
But it's October.
It feels like...
[AKANE]
Huh?
[YUTA] It feels like
I'm forgetting something.
[AKANE] Of course you are.
You've got amnesia.
[YUTA] True, but...
something's lacking.
[AKANE]
What is?
[YUTA]
It's hard to explain, but...
[AKANE]
Who cares about any of that?
[AKANE] If you're having fun,
then what does it matter?
[YUTA]
That's not what I mean.
I feel like there's
something I've gotta do.
And it's something even
more important than me?
No! It's important, even to you.
Something only I can do.
Something that I must do.
[gasps]
[AKANE]
Don't!
[UTSUMI]
Hot damn!
I've never bought so
much in my whole life!
Hold on. That's all
you're getting?
[AKANE] Yeah, I didn't really
see anything I wanted, so...
[UTSUMI]
Your loss. You know what?
I always wanted a friend
like you to hang out with!
You're so cool!
[AKANE]
Hey, you wanna come over?
[UTSUMI]
Huh?
[AKANE] Didn't you say that you
wanted to watch Ultra Force?
I've got Ultra Coliseum,
Nice, and Technicolor Q.
[UTSUMI]
But...
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
My folks aren't around.
You could even
stay if you want.
[UTSUMI]
This is wrong.
[AKANE]
Huh?
This would never
actually happen.
So many good things, one right
after another. But still...
Why now?
[TATSUMI]
It's finally summer break!
[HAYAKAWA] Those finals
really killed me, though.
[MARUSAN] Hey, Akane, let's all
go somewhere in the time off!
Yeah, that would be awesome!
My vote's for Sea.
[MARUSAN]
Sea again, really?
[FURUMA]
Yeah, Sea!
[TATSUMI]
I've got an annual pass!
Hey, Rikka, you coming, too?
I think I'll pass.
Aw, really? Why?
You have plenty of
friends to go with you.
Sure, but you're also
one of my friends.
Yeah, I know that. But still...
[AKANE gasps]
This is all a dream.
Here's your watch back.
Wouldn't it be better if you
could dream forever, though?
Dreams are things
you wake up from.
Everyone does.
Even you, Shinjo.
But if I could, I would stay
inside a dream forever.
[YUTA] I can't join you.
Gridman is calling me.
[UTSUMI] This is all a dream.
None of my friends are here.
[AKANE]
What about me?
Am I not your friend?
If this was how we
had actually met,
and like, if we had done this
stuff in real life some time,
then I think we could
have been friends.
[RIKKA]
This is a dream, right?
[AKANE]
What's wrong with a dream?
Let's keep it going,
just like this.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
But you have to!
I told you before!
You were born already
as my friend, Rikka.
And not just you,
but everybody else, too.
[RIKKA]
I'm sorry.
[MALE ANNOUNCER B]
Stopping next.
[AKANE] Even in dreams
I can't reach them?
[YUTA]
Utsumi! Rikka!
[UTSUMI]
Yuta! It's Yuta!
[RIKKA] Hibiki!
I remembered everything, too!
[YUTA] We have something.
Something only we can do!
Something we must do!
Right? Gridman?
[GRIDMAN] Right! I had faith,
and waited for you!
[GRIDMAN shouts]
[KAIJU roars]
What the...?
The kaiju materialized.
G-Grid kinesis?
Looks like Gridman only
woke up on the other side.
Meaning we've gotta deal
with this kaiju ourselves.
All right! Then let's shrink
down our output and go as four!
[ALL]
Access code...
[ANTI gasps]
[ALL] War God Combine!
Powered Zenon!
[ALL shouts]
Powered Breaker!
[ALL]
Powered Axe! Jumbo Saber. Slash!
[phone rings]
[CALIBUR]
What do you want?
[ANTI] The kaiju is gone now.
Why hasn't Gridman appeared?
[CALIBUR]
Because there's no need to.
G-Gridman will not be
facing you in battle.
[ANTI]
Why not?
[CALIBUR]
Because you're a living being
who possesses a heart.
[ANTI]
You're wrong. I am a kaiju!
What should I do now?
What should I...
[YUTA grunts]
[BORR cuckles]
Morning, sleepyheads.
Hey... Where's Gridman?!
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta, I'm right here.
Thanks so much, Gridman.
Because of you, we were able
to come back from the dream.
[GRIDMAN]
But there's another.
Another human who must
wake from their dream.
You mean Shinjo.
[RIKKA] Hey. There's something
I think all of you need to hear.
♪