♪
[STUDENTS chatter]
[YUTA] Hm.. It looks like
some of the clubs have
started preparing for
the festival already.
[RIKKA] Yeah, and I bet
my parents will show up.
Which'll suck.
I'm not excited for it either.
Our class project's lame.
[RIKKA]
Right? Anything but that.
[sighs] Whose idea was it
in the first place anyway?
Tonkawa and the others.
I see.
Hey.
[RIKKA, YUTA]
Hm?
[UTSUMI] Remember that
city-looking thing
we saw floating in the sky?
Yeah, I've been wondering
what that was.
It had city-like structures,
but it didn't look like a
place anyone would live in.
I think it could
be an alien base.
[ALEXIS] Hello, hello!
You may call me Alexis Kerib.
[UTSUMI] All the kaiju
appearances and city resets
might be that alien's doing.
[YUTA]
I dunno about that,
but he did have a sort
of "final boss" look.
[UTSUMI] If what that
kaiju girl said was true,
about there being
nothing outside the city,
then this whole place
might be isolated by--
[BORR] Hey! Enough with
the boring stories already.
Prattling on about kaiju
this and aliens that.
Shouldn't you kids be
studying or something?
[UTSUMI]
Huh?
[YUTA gasps] What are you
guys doing at our school?
And in outside shoes!
We're here because
of the enemy's
increased level of activity.
And besides, going to
school is normal.
[RIKKA] Uh, no.
Not for you, it isn't.
So, you believe that
alien isolated the city?
I do, like in
"The Vanishing City"!
Dancan's back, and-- Son of a--
You get way too excited whenever
your obsessions come up.
[UTSUMI]
What's wrong with that?
Even if we do know the reason,
we still don't know the goal.
This Akane Shinjo.
[YUTA] That alien I met
has got to be using her
to keep pumping out
all of these kaiju.
You really think so?
Don't you?
I'm not sure what I think.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[FEMALE STUDENT Agasps]
Who is that guy?
That's Calibur!
He sticks out like a
sore thumb, doesn't he?
[RIKKA] Think someone'll
call the police on him?
No, I'm pretty sure
he'll be fine.
The last time--
[MALE TEACHER A]
What business do you have here?
[FEMALE TEACHER A]
Please identify yourself.
[UTSUMI] It doesn't look
like he's fine to me!
[YUTA]
Uh-oh...
[MALE STUDENT A]
What's goin' on?
Ya know, I get the feeling
we should be leaving now.
Full retreat.
[BORR]
Hey, Calibur! It's time to go!
[CALIBUR]
Hm.
[TEACHERS gasp]
[VIT]
Well, see ya later.
[NAMIKO] Okay, spill!
Who were those guys?
Uh, the Neon Genesis
Junior High Students.
[HASS] That sounds like
a shitty band name.
[stomach growls]
She's not coming...
[AKANE grunts]
All done!
[ALEXIS]
Excellent work.
This Kaiju turned out
better than I expected.
[AKANE sighs]
Thanks.
I figured it was about time
to finally crush Gridman.
[AKANE]
Whoa, it's that late already?
[ALEXIS] Indeed.
Now let's get started.
Instance Abreatio--!
[AKANE]
Wait! Not just yet.
[YUTA] So Calibur and
the others ended up
getting reported after all.
[RIKKA]
You're kidding.
[UTSUMI] It's probably best they
stay away from school for a bit.
[RIKKA] The faculty is
cracking down on security
with the festival coming up.
Why are we even
having one this year?
[YUTA] Aren't school festivals
kind of an annual thing?
[UTSUMI] Not here. In fact, ours
hasn't had one in a few years.
[YUTA]
Huh.
[UTSUMI] But a buncha students
petitioned and brought it back.
Guess they wanted it real bad.
Sounds like our homeroom
teacher was all for it too.
[RIKKA] He kinda turned
over a new leaf, huh?
Before, he couldn't care
less about our class.
[UTSUMI]
You think...? Maybe.
[RIKKA]
It might be Gridman's influence.
Good morning!
Uh, hi, good morning.
[AKANE]
Hey, Rikka! C'mere a sec!
[RIKKA]
Hm?
[AKANE]
And Utsumi, you too!
What's with those faces?
Oh, that's right.
My secret's out now.
You know I'm the one
making the kaiju.
Because Hibiki told
you all, didn't he?
Not that I care.
[AKANE sighs]
But, hey...
Now I can show you what
I've been working on!
[YUTA]
That kaiju.
[AKANE] Yup! It's a powered-up
version of the first kaiju
you fought against.
Check it out!
It's like a scary mecha, huh?
I'm gonna let this one
loose during the festival.
I bet it'll tear up
the whole school.
But-- No, you can't do that!
Oh, really? Try to
stop me, If you can.
[FURUMA] What'cha got there?
It's so cute!
[AKANE giggles]
Did you make it, Akane?
Sure did. And a bunch
of others, too.
[FURUMA] That's awesome!
You're such a pro!
[AKANE giggles]
Oh, stop.
[MARUSAN]
It is kinda cute, in a way.
[FURUMA] Why aren't you
guys more impressed?
[UTSUMI]
That was a declaration of war.
[YUTA]
You're right.
But we've gotta find a
way to stop her somehow.
Obviously, postponing
the festival would be
the safest option, but...
There's no way we
can make that happen.
Man, this sucks! No one would
believe a monster's coming.
And it looked like a pretty
strong one, at that.
No matter! We can take it!
With our powers combined,
The Gridman Alliance
can do anything!
"With our powers combined."
[GRIDMAN] The larger I am,
the more energy is expended.
We couldn't maintain our
Access Flash for long.
What if the Neon Genesis
Junior High Students
put their powers together?
[UTSUMI]
Uh, we've tried that before
and they all
froze up, remember?
[YUTA]
No, hear me out.
What if we reduce both Gridman's
output size and theirs?
That... might... work!
Make 'em small enough so
everyone can fight at once!
[UTSUMI] That way, we can
get a full combine!
A full what now?
[UTSUMI]
It means we have a shot!
[RIKKA]
Before fighting...
...there are a few things
we should try first.
[UTSUMI] We'll never be able to
talk someone like Akane Shinjo
out of it.
So, what then?
We have to fight her?
[UTSUMI] We're just
figuring out what to do
in the likely event
that happens!
But trust me,
with a full combine,
that kaiju won't stand a--
Would you stop bringing
up this full combine thing?
It's almost like you're looking
for a fight at this point.
Do you have a better
solution to offer?
She flat-out said that she's
gonna unleash a kaiju
at the festival, so it's only
normal to come up with a plan.
And is it normal to
fight a classmate, too?
Because that's
the real issue here
and you keep
trying to ignore it.
Then what should we do?
You think she won't unleash
a deadly kaiju if we say,
"pretty please"?
What do you think, Gridman?
[GRIDMAN]
Both opinions are valid.
This conflict was
bound to happen.
That's a fancy way of
dodging the question.
[GRIDMAN]
I'm sorry.
Don't be, it's a
tough situation.
But we don't have time.
Like it or not, we're gonna
end up fighting this
Alexis thing one
way or another.
[RIKKA sisgh] Fine, then you
can count me out.
Hey, where are you going?
You can go ahead and do what
you think is right without me.
If you wanna fight, then fight.
Why are you so angry?
I'm not angry.
Yeah, you tell yourself that.
Hear me out.
It's not that I'm eager to
go and pick a fight with her,
but the Gridman Alliance
has no other option.
I've been wanting to
point this out for a while,
but only you call us
the Gridman Alliance.
What?
Anyway, fact is,
Akane's my friend.
I'll never be behind an idea
where we end up fighting her.
[UTSUMI sighs]
Man, this is a real pain.
You always let your emotions
do all the thinking for you.
[inhlaes]
[BORR]
Well that went terribly.
[UTSUMI]
I think I screwed up.
[YUTA]
Yup. Big time.
[UTSUMI groans] All the girls
at school are gonna think
I'm a huge ass from
now on! I'm done for.
My high school life barely
started and it's already over.
It's only second semester!
Listen man, I get that this
is a bad moment for you...
[UTSUMI] It is. But there's
no time for that!
Right now our focus needs
to be on Akane Shinjo.
[YUTA]
That's right.
If we don't do something quick,
it'll all end for good.
This time, we have to
stop her ourselves.
[AKANE] Are you for real?
You want me to "take it back"?
[YUTA]
If we're gonna fight,
let's do it at another
time and place.
[giggles]
Hold on a sec.
Are you actually
trying to stop me?
We'd like to know why
you'd target the festival.
It's because I hate it.
I know you guys don't want to
be part of the stupid thing
any more than I do.
And don't you think
seeing my kaiju in action
would be way cooler?
I know you do.
It doesn't make sense.
I thought you were
after Gridman.
Well, yeah, there's that, but...
In that case, there's no reason
put anyone else in harm's way.
Sorry, I'm leaving.
Got Phys. Ed next.
[YUTA]
No, wait!
[stomach growls]
[BORR]
That's one old sponge.
[ALL]
Hm?
[BORR]
Calibur, sit down.
You want somethin', or you
here to lose another fight?
Where is the girl?
I'm looking for her.
What girl?
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Oh, a customer?
Hm? Is there anything
I can get you?
That's not...
[RIKKA'S MOM]
Uh...?!
[RIKKA'S MOM] Here you are.
Sorry it's nothing fancy.
Uh... Okay. Is this
kid a friend of yours?
I assure you he's not.
I mean, does he look
like he'd be our friend?
--[RIKKA'S MOM] Mm-hm.
--[VIT gasps]
[MAX] Why didn't you
chase him down before?
You could have defeated him.
Felt like Yuta
wouldn't let me.
[MAX]
Hm.
[BORR]
I'm gonna stop you right there.
You have something
to say to Mama?
Or do I need to
teach you manners?
Hey!
[CALIBUR]
You have a phone, right?
[BORR]
Huh?
[CALIBUR]
All right. You can go.
[BORR]
Don't just let him walk away!
I got his cell number. You can
teach him some manners later.
[gasps]
Hey, Max! Aren't you
gonna step in?
This guy has some screws loose!
[MAX sighs]
[BORR] Don't you give
me that lazy shrug.
Hibiki told me everything.
How you were the one who
killed Tonkawa and the others.
It wasn't me.
It was my kaiju that
killed all of those girls.
So you're fine with what
you've been causing?
[AKANE] Kaiju are what
make this city go 'round.
Sometimes it has to be fixed.
Besides, did you even
get along with Tonkawa
and the other girls?
I wouldn't say that I
didn't get along with them.
So it's same with
or without them.
It's not the same.
Then why don't you
just kill me?
That'd settle everything,
wouldn't it?
No, that wouldn't
settle anything.
[chuckles] I always knew
you were a good girl.
So different from
the rest of them.
You're the person who
should be close to me.
I'm the what?
Wouldn't you like to
get along with a god?
You might as well accept it:
no matter what I do,
you'll never be able to hate me.
I made sure you were
set up to be that way.
[RIKKA gasps]
[AKANE] Everyone who lives
here has no choice but to love
everything about me.
That's why you and I
are friends, Rikka.
Are you saying I was born
already as your friend?
[AKANE]
That's right.
You were made to be my friend
when you were made by my kaiju.
[ANNOUNCER]
Departing. Please hold on.
[RIKKA]
The festival is tomorrow.
[RIKKA] I tried talking
to Akane earlier today,
but it was useless.
I couldn't stop her.
I've been thinking.
That junk computer and the
shop belong to my parents.
So in a way, I haven't
contributed anything myself.
[YUTA]
I don't think that's true.
We've only been able to
get this far because everyone
was working together.
There have been plenty of
times that we wouldn't have
made it if you weren't with us.
I know Utsumi feels
that way. And me.
I want you to be here with--!
Tomorrow!
I'm going to
apologize to Utsumi.
Huh? But he was the one who
said all of the nasty stuff.
[RIKKA]
I want to apologize first.
How come?
That guy. You know him.
He'd never expect me
to make the first move.
[gasps]
The first move. That's it!
[dog barks]
[ALEXIS] The school
festival is tomorrow, yes?
[AKANE]
Mm.
[ALEXIS] You don't seem
too excited about it.
Oh, that isn't true at all.
I absolutely am.
[ALEXIS]
That's wonderful to hear!
I'm sure everybody
is looking forward
to seeing your big performance.
[AKANE]
Well, yeah.
[ALEXIS] Hopefully, they will
all enjoy the show.
Lots of guests will be
coming from all over.
That's exactly
why I can't lose.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Do it. Now's the time.
Very well. Instance Abreactio--
[AKANE]
Wait...! What's going on?
[STUDENTS scream]
[STUDENTS gaspsing]
[FEMALE STUDENT A gasps]
Look at that thing!
Deploying Gridman first
to prompt an evacuation.
Not a bad idea.
This way, Shinjo has less of a
reason to attack the school,
am I right?
[AKANE] They sure do
know how to ruin the fun.
Now, Alexis!
[ALEXIS]
Instance Abreaction!
[KAIJU roars]
[AKANE]
Huh? What gives?
Gridman is only half
his usual size today!
[ALEXIS]
Seems they're undermining you!
Now then, let's join the battle!
[ALL]
Access code...!
Wait. Is it okay
to all go at once?
Uh, they shrunk
their output scale.
Now they can avoid the
interference problems they
experienced before.
I don't really get it.
[UTSUMI sighs]
I don't have to get it,
as long as they win.
[UTSUMI]
They probably will.
No-- They definitely will!
[roars]
[VIT grunts]
Close one!
[BORR grunts]
Get ready! Today is the day
you will witness my full power!
[GRIDMAN] Now is when we
put our powers together!
[ALL]
Right!
[ALL] Hyperlink Combine.
Full Powered Gridman!
[AKANE] What the hell is that?
You just made a bigger robot.
My kaiju will never lose
to something like that!
[KAIJU, GRIDMAN grunting]
Wow! You see that?
Yeah!
[GRIDMAN]
Twin Drill Break!
[GRIDMAN shouts]
[GRIDMAN grunts]
[GRIDMAN]
Full power... Charge!
Grid... Full Power... Finish!
[KAIJU stammers]
[BYSTANDERS gasp]
[FESTIVAL GOERS chattering]
So, Utsumi. I, uh...
[gasps] I'm sorry about the
other day! I was an idiot!
[RIKKA]
Yeah, I'm sorry too.
[BOTH laugh]
[RIKKA]
That looks good on you.
[UTSUMI]
Doesn't it?
[UTSUMI] Anyway. Did Shinjo
decide to show up?
[RIKKA] Marusan! Did Akane
come to school today?
Huh? I didn't see her around!
I think she said she
wasn't feeling well!
Is that so? 'Kay thanks!
[AKANE]
You might as well accept it.
No matter what I do,
you'll never be able to hate me.
[HASS]
Oh, Rikka.
[NAMIKO]
Ah! There she is! Hey, girl!
Your mom was looking for you!
Hi! Ugh... Those are outfits
are uh, interesting.
Thanks.
[NAMIKO] Also, my tea ceremony
starts in like, 20 minutes!
[RIKKA]
Okay! Let's head over.
[HASS]
It'll be shit tea.
[NAMIKO]
That is just plain rude.
[YUTA, UTSUMI gasp]
[UTSUMI] Oh yeah, we've gotta
hand out the flyer, huh?
[YUTA]
Yup.
♪
I lost another battle. If I
keep losing, my city is...
[ALEXIS] I know that you can
do so much better than this.
After all, you're brimming
with talent.