[distant band warms up]
[FEMALE TRACK MANAGER A]
Twenty-three! Twenty-four!
Twenty-five! Twenty-six!
You've got this, Narisako!
Twenty-nine! Thirty! Thirty-one!
Thirty-two! Thirty-three!
Thirty-four! Come on ladies!
Thirty-five!
[explosion]
[RIKKA humming]
[humming continues]
Oh. You're awake.
Good morning. If it is.
You were out for almost half an
hour and I couldn't wake you up.
Do you feel alright?
[YUTA] Um. I'm not in
pain or anything.
[RIKKA]
You had me nervous.
Collapsing and passing
out like that.
Want to wash up?
Over there. Bathroom's that way.
[YUTA]
Who is that girl?
And for that matter,
who am I?
What's going on?
I can't remember anything.
Does that mean...
Did I lose my memory?
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta!
[YUTA]
Yuta?
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta!
[YUTA]
Is that my name?
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta!
[YUTA]
A computer?
[gasps]
[GRIDMAN] I am a
Hyper Agent. Gridman.
Cool. I think. Nice to
meet you, Gridman.
[GRIDMAN] You have to
remember your calling.
Wait, I have a calling?
What're you doing?
[YUTA]
I'm just talking with this guy.
[RIKKA]
Who?
[YUTA]
Gridman.
[RIKKA]
There's nothing on the screen.
[YUTA]
Huh? He's right there.
[RIKKA]
Huh?
[YUTA]
Only I can see him?
Wait. Does that mean
I'm hallucinating?
'Kay, Hibiki.
You're acting weird.
Gridman told me I had to
remember what my calling is.
Your calling? Like what
you're called?
No, something else I think.
Huh? Then what do you mean?
Where are we, anyway?
Home. But to you, it's the shop.
Whose?
Mine, of course!
Yeah, but that
doesn't tell me who.
"Doesn't tell you?"
Who do you mean by who?
Who, you.
[RIKKA groans]
Look. Don't screw with me.
What? I'm not kidding!
I can't remember.
You, this place, anything.
You're serious?
A total blank.
Like memory loss?
Right! That's it!
Don't screw with me.
[RIKKA'S MOTHER] Rikka. Do me a
favor and stop being so loud.
[RIKKA]
Mama.
Maybe it's a good idea
for you to walk him
over to the hospital.
Huh? Why me?
Oh, I'm sorry. Aren't you two
in the same class together?
Aw...
If he's suffering memory loss,
it could mean he hit
his head on something.
[RIKKA] You really don't look so
good.
You're telling me. I keep
seeing and hearing things.
[YUTA]
The mist sure is thick.
[RIKKA]
Is it?
[YUTA]
It doesn't feel normal.
[gasps]
What is it now?
[YUTA]
Behind you! Up there!
There's a kaiju! It's humongous!
[RIKKA]
Huh? Where at?
[YUTA]
Just beyond the mist!
[RIKKA]
I don't see anything.
[YUTA] No, no no.
I see it! It's right there!
[RIKKA sighs] Let's get moving
before the hospital closes.
[RIKKA]
Hey, if you lost your memory,
does that mean you don't
remember anything
that happened today?
[YUTA]
Nope.
[RIKKA]
I see. Okay.
But, if you are just
pretending to have amnesia,
then you really suck.
Uh. Did something happen?
So how did it go?
A lot of it went over my head,
but they said I'd be back
to normal before long.
Least there's that.
Oh, hey, do you even
have an insurance card?
Insurance?
[RIKKA sighs]
You can go home, right?
[YUTA] Mm. Thanks for
taking care of me.
[RIKKA]
Hm?
[YUTA]
Well, see you.
[RIKKA]
See you.
What's wrong?
I don't exactly
know where to go.
[RIKKA gasps] You forgot
your home address too?
Well, I don't have a clue
where you live either.
[gasps] Wait, hand me
your cell phone.
[YUTA]
Oh, right.
[RIKKA]
I'll text Utsumi.
He could probably
be able to help out.
Ah, okay. Yeah. I know
where this is. Got it.
But it's pretty far from here.
You don't say.
On top of that,
it's already seven!
[RIKKA groans]
[RIKKA]
And I am starving.
Why was I sleeping at
some girl's house anyway?
I'm not just some girl.
The name's Rikka Takarada.
[YUTA]
Hm?
And, Hibiki, we found you lying
unconscious in front of our
place and nothing we
did could wake you.
What do you mean?
Uh, do we have a history?
Are we friends?
[sighs]
Got a newsflash.
Today is the most we've
ever spoken to each other
since we were put into
the same classroom.
Oh, I see.
That hit the spot.
[YUTA]
Uh?
Whoa... What's up with him?
Should I leave you here?
Huh? No, I'm ready to go.
[YUTA]
This is the address.
[RIKKA]
Awesome. I'll be off then.
Utsumi said he'd come by and
pick you up tomorrow morning.
[YUTA]
Great. Thanks for everything.
[RIKKA]
Bye.
[YUTA]
I'm home.
It's dark...
[YUTA]
After looking around the house,
I discovered my parents
were on a business trip.
They wouldn't return
home for three months.
[YUTA] It seemed unreal,
like someone else's life.
[YUTA]
Gridman. Does he exist?
[YUTAQ]
Or was it a hallucination?
[YUTA] You wouldn't happen
to be Utsumi, would you?
It looks like you
weren't kidding
about having memory loss.
You don't even remember
my face, do you?
I'm sorry, no.
[UTSUMI]
Whatever.
We only started getting to
know each other in April.
We'll pretend we've just
become friends again.
[YUTA]
Thanks. So um...
[UTSUMI]
What is it?
[YUTA] You know...
What kind of person am I?
[UTSUMI] That's a heavy question
to suddenly drop on me.
What kind of person
are you? Let's see...
I'd describe you as... regular.
Not a bad guy at all.
[YUTA] By the way, you wouldn't
happen to have heard of
something called Gridman?
[UTSUMI]
Nope. Is it a new trend?
[YUTA]
I wouldn't say that.
So get this,
yesterday when I was...
[NAMIKO] Guess what?
I saw you two yesterday.
[gasps]
You were walking
side-by-side with Hibiki.
[HASS]
He's a boy.
Yeah? So what's the big deal?
Thanks again for everything.
[NAMIKO] Aw! You two
are gonna get married!
[RIKKA]
I can't breathe!
Your desk is
back there. By her.
You're so slender, I'm jealous.
[giggles] I don't know
if I would agree!
[school bells ringing]
[RIKKA]
Hey.
[YUTA]
Hm?
[RIKKA] Look, my friends
are giving me hard time
when you're around.
[YUTA] I get it. So I should
probably avoid talking to you.
[RIKKA] I never said that.
Just give me some space.
[YUTA] Sorry, I don't
know what you mean.
Ugh, never mind.
[TONKAWA grunts]
[TONKAWA giggles]
Let's eat lunch outside.
Uh. I didn't pack anything.
Because of your memory loss?
Yep. My brain's at its limit
just dealing with school.
[AKANE]
Here you go.
[YUTA]
Uh...
I bet you're starving.
But you're not the type to
let on, are you, Hibiki?
Like a samurai.
I'm sorry, you're...?
Akane Shinjo.
You know, it's almost like
you're a new student.
Since you can't
remember anything.
That's right. I can't
remember anything at all.
This is a special dog.
I've got two, so one is yours.
That's really nice of you.
--[AKANE] Not at all.
--[TONKAWA] Whoa! Heads up!
[PA chimes]
[PA ANNOUNCER]
Paging Inui,
you have a telephone
call on line one.
Inui, you have a
Please come to the
staff room immediately.
[UTSUMI, YUTA]
Aww...
[TONKAWA gasps] I
am so incredibly sorry!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, no damage done.
[AKANE, MARUSAN]
Go do that outside, Tonkawa!
I'll think about my mistake!
There, I'm done!
What about your special dog?
[YUTA]
It's just a little smooshed.
I'm sure it' still delicious.
That's the classroom's ball,
not mine.
[TOIKO] You're missing
the point entirely.
[giggles]
[ALEXIS]
Sculpting another Kaiju?
Something bad
must have happened.
Something you're
unable to let go of.
[UTSUMI]
Today was pretty rough.
Yeah. But Shinjo sure
was nice to me, huh?
I hate to break it to you,
but there's a difference between
being nice and taking
pity on someone.
[YUTA chuckles]
Hey, let's not split hairs.
[UTSUMI] No. Let's!
Akane Shinjo is a double threat.
With an arsenal of
both looks and talent.
She's a gift to humanity.
Someone the whole
class worships!
[YUTA] You don't have a crush
on her, do you, Utsumi?
[UTSUMI]
Wha-- N-No!
Personally, I find her
way too unapproachable.
I could never see us together.
But never mind her!
I wanna meet this Gridman guy
you were telling me about!
The thing is...
[UTSUMI]
Hm?
[RIKKA]
Mm?
Hey. Where'd Tonkawa run off to?
Outside. If I know her,
she's probably skipping.
That girl always slacks off
whenever Yotsuba isn't around.
[RIKKA]
I'm home!
Ugh...
Don't use the front door.
I thought you were a customer.
Well what if told you I brought
a couple of those along with me?
Sorry to bother you again.
[RIKKA'S MOTHER]
Ah, the boy from yesterday.
How are you?
Everything still a fog?
Yeah, but I'm feeling alright.
[RIKKA'S MOTHER]
That's great.
Rikka! Keep an eye on the shop.
I have to head out
and run a few errands.
[RIKKA grunts]
Nobody's going to stop by.
[RIKKA'S MOTHER]
Excuse me?
[RIKKA]
Oh, did you hear that?
[RIKKA'S MOTHER] You're getting
cold tofu for supper.
[RIKKA]
Mama.
You and your mom sure
seem to be close.
[RIKKA grunts]
What do you mean?
I think we're pretty normal.
[UTSUMI] Yuta! Which one
of these has Gridman?
That big computer there.
[UTSUMI]
Wow. You weren't kidding.
Check out the size
of this relic.
Looks cobbled together.
What a pile of junk, huh?
[GRIDMAN]
I am a Hyper Agent. Grid.
[YUTA] Yeah I know.
You told me yesterday.
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta, you have to hurry.
There is danger closing
in on this world.
[YUTA]
What kind of danger?
[UTSUMI]
Who are you talking to?
You don't see
Gridman either, Utsumi?
[UTSUMI]
Should I?
I'm the only one.
[YUTA]
Huh? What do you mean?
This doesn't look good.
Definitely not good.
[GRIDMAN]
The danger is almost upon you!
[ALEXIS] You've given it such
a nice and emotive form.
Now, to put it in motion.
Instance Abreaction!
[YUTA gasps]
What is it?
I don't know for certain, But I
got a feeling there's trouble.
[UTSUMI] Mm. You've been
troubled all day.
No. Something else.
[KAIJU roars]
I hear a kaiju nearby.
Yeah, I'm thinking we should
take you back to the hospital.
[CROWD screaming]
[RIKKA'S MOTHER]
Is there a fire?
For real?
[NEWS STATIONS chatter]
[FIREFIGHTER A]
Attention!
Please do not flee in the
direction of the kaiju!
[CROWD screaming]
[TRAIN ANNOUNCER A] The train
has come to an unexpected stop.
We apologize for
any inconvenience
this may have caused.
Something's over there.
I've gotta see!
[YUTA]
Utsumi!
[RIKKA gasps]
[roars]
[UTSUMI]
No mistaking it.
That thing's
a real-life kaiju.
Is that the same one you
mentioned seeing the other day?
I'm not entirely sure.
[UTSUMI] We can't make
out anything from here.
Let's head to the main road.
[YUTA]
No way, it's too dangerous!
Whoa!
[RIKKA grunts]
[TONKAWA]
Huh?
It blew up our school.
[RADION STATIONS chatter]
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta! Yuta!
Gridman's calling me.
[YUTA grunts]
--[RIKKA] Hibiki!
--[UTSUMI] Yuta!
I'm here, Gridman!
You called out to me, right?
[GRIDMAN] Correct. The time has
come for you and I to awaken.
To awaken? What does that--?
[GRIDMAN]
I'll explain later!
What?! But it's
happening right now--
Yuta!
Whoa! What the...?
For the record, we both saw
Junk swallow Yuta whole, right?
Who knew that old computers
were so terrifying?
I see something on the screen.
Whatever it is,
I'm seeing it too.
[KAIJU A roars]
Look!
No way. A giant robot?
Is that the Gridman
Yuta was talking about?
We can't make anything
out from this far away!
[YUTA] I know what I must do.
This Kaiju has to be stopped.
I think Yuta's voice
just came out of Junk.
[YUTA (GRIDMAN) grunts]
[KAIJU A roars]
[roars]
[UTSUMI]
He's transformed.
When he got sucked up,
Yuta became Gridman.
He's defending the city
against the kaiju!
[RIKKA]
Junk's going haywire!
[UTSUMI] Old computers are
cooler than I ever imagined!
Wait. You don't suppose
Junk is somehow
connected to Gridman, do you?
What if it's telling us
that he's in trouble?
[groans] If only this
was the Ultra series!
Then the kaiju would have
some kind of weak point!
[RIKKA]
Uh. You lost me.
[YUTA]
Damn it! Why can't I move?
[UTSUMI exhales]
[UTSUMI]
Found it.
The neck is weaker than
the rest of its body!
If he goes after it...
[RIKKA] We have to tell
Hibiki right away!
[UTSUMI]
Well, yeah. But how?
[RIKKA]
Uh...
[YUTA] The school!
The school's on fire!
[RIKKA]
You're kidding!
We can hear him fine,
but he's not reading us.
Isn't there some
way to contact him?
[UTSUMI]
Maybe through the computer?
It's the best option we have.
Tell me what we should say,
and I'll type it on
the keyboard, Utsumi.
[UTSUMI grunts]
Dang she's fast.
[YUTA (GRIDMAN)]
I hear you.
[YUTA]
Rikka and Utsumi.
[YUTA (GRIDMAN)]
Loud and clear!
[roars]
[YUTA (GRIDMAN) grunts]
Amazing...
Go, Gridman! Take him down!
[YUTA (GRIDMAN)]
Grid...
...Beam!
[UTSUMI]
He did it! Yes! We won!
[BOTH gasp]
[UTSUMI] Hey, are you okay?
Say something!
I... Guess I'm back.
That was amazing, Yuta!
You fought a kaiju and won!
We saw the whole thing!
I can't take all of the credit.
[GRIDMAN]
Yuta!
[YUTA, UTSUMI]
Hm?
[GRIDMAN] Yuta, you must
complete your mission.
[YUTA]
But I thought I just did.
[GRIDMAN]
This is only the beginning.
[YUTA gasps]
Okay, pause!
Did the three of us and
Gridman just beat that thing?
[YUTA]
Uh... Yeah.
That makes us a team,
which means we need to come
up with a name for our group!
I'm thinking of something like,
"The Gridman Alliance".
I hate to say this, but I'm
finished for today.
[UTSUMI]
Huh?
[RIKKA] My head feels
completely scrambled.
I still don't know who
or what Gridman is.
Plus, I'm worried about
whether my friends are safe.
I'm sorry, but right now...
Oh... Think we should go?
[RIKKA'S MOTHER]
Rikka!
Oh. Thank goodness
you kids are okay!
Honestly. Would it have killed
you to answer your phone?
[RIKKA]
Huh?
[RIKKA'S MOTHER]
Don't "huh" me, young lady.
I was in a panic.
Yeah, we should probably go.
[YUTA]
Mm.
Coming up next,
reactions from eye-witnesses.
[MALE REPORTER]
The question remains,
where did the
beast come from?
[FEMALE REPORTER]
What did you do?
After it started
heading your way?
[ALEXIS] It would appear we had
some unexpected company show up.
[UTSUMI] Whoa. You see what
I see? Or am I just crazy?
I could have sworn the school
burnt down yesterday.
What's up?
Oh, uh. Well, look.
Whoa... No way...
[RIKKA]
The school's back to normal.
[YUTA]
Something weird is going on.
[UTSUMI, RIKKA]
Uh-huh.