[ALEXIS] Wow. How wonderful!
Are you going to the pool?
[AKANE] It's for a field trip.
[ALEXIS] Oh?
[AKANE] We're traveling to the
mountains,
[ALEXIS] Well, that sounds fun.
[AKANE] I wonder.
[ALEXIS] This wouldn't have
happened if you
[AKANE] You're still on about
that?
[ALEXIS] Is that so?
[ALEXIS] By the way, what's this
kaiju?
[AKANE] Well, there's an
experiment I want
[ALEXIS] I knew you were
enjoying this.
[YUTA] It's not here.
[YUTA] Found it!
[UTSUMI] It's so hot.
[UTSUMI]
[YUTA] Sorry, for being late!
[ANNOUNCER] Your attention
please.
[UTSUMI] You're slow.
[UTSUMI] The train's here.
[YUTA] Yeah.
[YUTA] Whoa.
[YUTA] I had no idea the river
was this
[UTSUMI] It is pretty large.
[YUTA] Guess you're right.
[UTSUMI] Though, they pretty
much become
[YUTA] Wait.
[UTSUMI] I almost forgot, your
amnesia and
[YUTA] So tired.
[YUTA] Shoot!
[ANNOUNCER] The doors are
closing.
[UTSUMI]
[UTSUMI] That was one heck of a
close call.
[YUTA] We must have really been
knocked
[HASS]
[NAMIKO]
[RIKKA]
[YUTA]
[RIKKA] Seriously?
[NAMIKO] Yeah?
[HASS] Girl, eating granola
won't help you
[YUTA]
[NAMIKO] You're kidding.
[HASS] Fasting is the key.
[NAMIKO] But I love food too
much.
[STUDENTS]
[TEACHER] Class!
[YUTA] Wow.
[TATSUMI] I bet it's sick.
[TEACHER] And don't forget to
put your
[HAYAKAWA] Imagine, a goddess
like Akane
[UTSUMI] Yes, sir.
[ONDA] Yes, sir.
[TATSUMI] Yes, sir.
[HAYAKAWA] Yes, sir.
[TATSUMI] You move like a sloth.
[ONDA] We'll start calling you
Slowkawa.
[TATSUMI] Yeah, Onda.
[ONDA]
[YUTA] Utsumi.
[UTSUMI]
[YUTA] You're looking a little
bit pudgy.
[UTSUMI] What did you say?
[YUTA] Stop!
[FEMALE STUDENTS ]
[NAMIKO] We're going ahead!
[RIKKA] Okay!
[RIKKA]
[AKANE] Could you rub some on my
back?
[RIKKA] Sure.
[RIKKA] Your skin's so pretty.
[AKANE] That's because I stay
out of the sun.
[RIKKA] You have no scars or
anything.
[RIKKA
'kay, I'm all done.
[AKANE] Now the front.
[RIKKA]
[AKANE] Got you.
[GUIDE C] All right, uh.
[YUTA] Okay!
[UTSUMI] Sure.
[HASS] Alright!
[NAMIKO] Alright!
[RIKKA] Okay!
[AKANE] Okay!
[TATSUMI] Uh-huh!
[HAYAKAWA] Sure!
[ONDA] Okay!
[STUDENTS] Okay!
[GUIDE C] We'll start by
practicing a forward
[STUDENTS]
[UTSUMI]
[NAMIKO] So soft!
[HASS] Feels so good!
[UTSUMI] Quit pawing me, you
idiots!
[HASS] But you're so squishy.
[NAMIKO] You need to try this,
Rikka!
[UTSUMI]
[RIKKA] Ugh, so not gonna
happen.
[AKANE] How soft is he?
[UTSUMI]
[AKANE] It does feel good!
[GUIDE C] Did everyone hear all
that?
[YUTA] We didn't, sorry!
[RIKKA] One, two!
[AKANE] One, two!
[NAMIKO] One, two!
[HASS] One, two!
[GUIDE B] Good!
[GUIDE A] Yeah!
[UTSUMI]
[MALE STUDENT A]
[MALE STUDENT B]
[AKANE]
[RIKKA]
[NAMIKO]
[HASS]
[RIKKA] And up!
[NAMIKO] And up!
[AKANE]
[AKANE] I knew this would suck!
[RIKKA] Akane.
[AKANE] Perfectly fine!
[GUIDE B] All right, everyone.
[STUDENTS]
[NAMIKO] What are they even
doing?
[HASS] Some kind of sumo game.
[TATSUMI]
[MALE STUDENT B]
[ONDA] Hey, get it together,
Tatsumi!
[STUDENTS ]
[RIKKA] Yeah, get it together!
[NAMIKO] Yeah, get it together!
[STUDENTS ]
[MAX] Don't you like her?
[ONDA] Keep it up, you're gonna
be a
[YUTA]
[AKANE] What's this?
[YUTA] I don't know if that's
exactly it.
[AKANE] Everyone else sure is
having a ball.
[YUTA] Yeah.
[AKANE] To be honest, I'm not so
good at
[HAYAKAWA] He's not talking to
us.
[TATSUMI]
[ONDA]
[YUTA] Is that so?
[AKANE] Are you kidding?
[YUTA] I just always pictured
you as able to
[AKANE] No way.
[AKANE] A while ago, like during
first
[MALE STUDENT C] So you two are
pretty
[RIKKA] She loves me!
[AKANE] But lately, it's been
just one bad
[YUTA] Lately?
[HASS] Let go of my face!
[MALE STUDENT C]
[AKANE] Yeah.
[YUTA] People problems, or
something?
[AKANE] Sure, but there's more
to it than that.
[YUTA] Things you must do?
[AKANE] That's right.
[AKANE]
[YUTA]
[AKANE] So how's your memory?
[YUTA] Nope, not yet.
[AKANE] Not at all?
[YUTA] No.
[AKANE] That's gotta be hard on
you.
[YUTA] Yeah, but it's not
terrible.
[AKANE] I hope you remember
soon.
[YUTA] Same.
[AKANE] But you're transforming,
aren't
[YUTA] Yeah.
[AKANE] See ya!
[YUTA]
[AKANE] I knew I was right about
him!
[AKANE] Ah.
[AKANE] Please!
[ALEXIS] Very well!
[YUTA] It's ringing?
[UTSUMI] What's going on?
[STUDENTS]
[GUIDE B] Everyone, get away
from the river!
[HASS] The entire landscape is
moving!
[NAMIKO] No, it's a kaiju!
[RIKKA] There any chance that's
not a kaiju?
[YUTA] It's as big as a
mountain.
[UTSUMI] No.
[STUDENTS]
[UTSUMI] Hold up.
[AKANE] Right!
[ALEXIS] To think of
overwhelming him with
[AKANE] I know it's sorta cheap
to scale up,
[AKANE] Your move, Gridman.
[KAIJU A]
[BORR]
[CALIBUR] I think we have too
much time on
[BORR]
[RIKKA'S MOM] Do any of you
actually have
[RIKKA'S MOM] Hey, I asked if
you're
[VIT] Well, you see we work, and
then we
[RIKKA'S MOM] What?
[MAX] Gone with who to where?
[RIKKA'S MOM] Rikka and the boys
went on a
[MAX] A field trip, you say?
[UTSUMI] Shoot, what now?
[YUTA] But without Junk here,
there's no way
[RIKKA] And going back to the
shop is out of
[UTSUMI] Then our only option is
to call
[YUTA] Yeah, you're right!
[RIKKA] Well, what're we waiting
f-?
[YUTA] We don't have our cell
phones.
[UTSUMI] They're inside our
lockers!
[YUTA] Then we've got to go back
and get
[RIKKA] But it's that way,
right?
[UTSUMI] Unless someone has a
better idea.
[TEACHER] Kids, quick!
[STUDENTS] Ex.
[YUTA] I have to go!
[UTSUMI] I'm coming too!
[YUTA] Rikka, leave with the
others!
[UTSUMI]
[NAMIKO] Come on, Rikka!
[HASS] What the hell is she
doing just
[UTSUMI] Go this way!
[YUTA] Right!
[HASS] Rikka!
[NAMIKO] Rikka!
[KAIJU A]
[YUTA] Shinjo?
[UTSUMI] Yeah, I didn't see her
back there!
[UTSUMI] It's not what you
think!
[YUTA]
[AKANE] But you're transforming,
aren't
[AKANE] He's so slow.
[YUTA]
[KAIJU A]
[UTSUMI] Shit!
[YUTA] They said it was supposed
to be a five
[UTSUMI] Five kilometers?
[YUTA] There!
[UTSUMI] A telephone!
[YUTA] Wait.
[UTSUMI] Leave it to me!
[YUTA] Yeah!
[UTSUMI] Now, make the call!
[YUTA] Uh.
[UTSUMI] No.
[RIKKA] Hey!
[UTSUMI]
[YUTA]
[RIKKA]
[YUTA] Rikka!
[UTSUMI] Rikka!
[RIKKA] If it's our shop's phone
number.
[RIKKA] Um, hello, mama?
[MAX] I understand.
[MAX] I'd like to make a
purchase.
[MAX] How much for this unit?
[RIKKA'S MOM] Like to buy?
[RIKKA'S MOM] It's thirty-seven
thousand
[VIT] So pricey!
[BORR] So pricey!
[MAX] Empty your pockets!
[RIKKA'S MOM] Whoa!
[MAX] We won't be needing a
receipt.
[RIKKA] Great news!
[YUTA] Awesome, thanks!
[UTSUMI] Quick!
[YUTA]
[AKANE] It should've been long
enough since
[AKANE] So why is Gridman taking
his sweet
[AKANE] What the heck?
[AKANE] Well, this totally
sucks.
[AKANE]
[AKANE] What are you doing here?
[ANTI] Get on.
[ANTI]
[YUTA]
[UTSUMI]
[UTSUMI] You can't be serious.
[UTSUMI] Of course this happens
when we're
[YUTA] Ugh.
[UTSUMI] Yeah, but.
[RIKKA]
[RIKKA] Hibiki.
[YUTA] Leave you?
[RIKKA] Seems like I'm the one
holding you
[YUTA]
[RIKKA] Go ahead.
[YUTA] Alright then.
[UTSUMI]
[YUTA] I'll see you when you get
there!
[UTSUMI] Right!
[YUTA]
[KAIJU A]
[YUTA] I've gotta keep moving.
[YUTA]
[MAX] Wake up!
[CALIBUR]
[VIT]
[BORR] What are you sleeping
for?
[VIT] You were the one sleeping,
not me.
[BORR] Yes, you were!
[CALIBUR] I slept well.
[ANNOUNCER] The train is about
to depart.
[MAX] Unload Junk, quickly!
[MAX] We were this close to
missing our
[CALIBUR]
[RIKKA]
[UTSUMI] I wonder if Yuta
reached the station
[UTSUMI]
[RIKKA] Isn't that his life
jacket?
[UTSUMI] No.
[VIT] Wow, now that's an
inferno.
[BORR] We came all this way and
they've got
[CALIBUR] There's not much time.
[YUTA] Hey!
[BORR] Put on some damn clothes.
[MAX] He's here.
[YUTA] Thanks for coming out,
guys.
[CALIBUR] Let's connect Junk.
[VIT] Is this the only solution?
[BORR] You've gotta do what
you've gotta
[GRIDMAN] Where is this?
[YUTA] I'll explain later!
[GRIDMAN] Of course!
[YUTA] Good to hear.
[KAIJU A]
[YUTA] Can you grow to match its
size
[GRIDMAN] Even at my largest
output, my
[GRIDMAN] Plus, the larger I am,
the more
[YUTA] So what do we do?
[BORR] Hey!
[YUTA]
[BORR] I'll lend you a hand, so
get your ass
[YUTA] Right!
[BORR] And access code.
[BORR] Buster Borr!
[GRIDMAN]
[KAIJU A]
[UTSUMI] Look, Gridman made it!
[RIKKA] Then that means Hibiki's
alright!
[ANTI]
[AKANE] Finally, he's here!
[BORR] Shit!
[VIT] Wow, surprisingly
delicate, huh?
[KAIJU A]
[BORR] Forest Extinguisher
Missile, Go!
[KAIJU A]
[YUTA] Bring it!
[GRIDMAN] We will not lose!
[KAIJU A]
[GRIDMAN]
[AKANE]
[AKANE] It stinks.
[KAIJU A]
[GRIDMAN]
[ANTI] Gridman!
[ANTI] Today's the day I defeat
you!
[GRIDMAN] You again?
[ANTI] That's right!
[GRIDMAN]
[ANTI]
[ANTI] Today's the day!
[GRIDMAN]
[UTSUMI] Looks like no battle
royale this
[BORR] Sydney Super Adhesive
Missile!
[ANTI] What the hell?
[BORR] Sit quiet there for a
bit.
[GRIDMAN] Right!
[GRIDMAN] Full Armor Combine!
[BORR] Full Armor Combine!
[GRIDMAN] Buster Gridman!
[BORR] Buster Gridman!
[AKANE] He combined with another
one of
[GRIDMAN] Buster Grid Missile!
[ANTI] Don't get full of
yourself!
[GRIDMAN]
[BORR]
[VIT] Huh.
[MAX] A copy ability?
[ANTI] Disappear!
[BORR] Forget the small fry!
[GRIDMAN] Right!
[KAIJU A]
[BORR] Twin Buster.
[GRIDMAN] Grid.
[GRIDMAN] Beam!
[BORR] Beam!
[KAIJU A]
[ANTI] Disappear!
[AKANE] Huh.
[MAX] Good work.
[BORR] Yep.
[VIT] You know they're just for
show.
[CALIBUR]
[YUTA]
[RIKKA] Hibiki!
[UTSUMI] Yuta!
[RIKKA]
[UTSUMI] You're alright!
[YUTA] I'm fine, thanks.
[BORR] True that, but we all
know it was
[GRIDMAN] Let's continue to
combine our
[GRIDMAN] By the way, where are
we?
[UTSUMI] I'm just glad I had
spare change
[RIKKA]
[RIKKA] What's that kid doing
out here?
[TEACHER] We were worried sick
about you!
[YUTA] Yeah.
[UTSUMI]
[RIKKA] We kinda got lost along
the way.
[NAMIKO] So, tell us, Rikka.
[HASS]
[NAMIKO] Were you hanging out
with the
[RIKKA] I, uh, can't hear a
single word you're
[UTSUMI] She's gone.
[HASS]
[NAMIKO] If you're looking for
Akane, she
[UTSUMI]
[NAMIKO] They've already got
them back up
[UTSUMI]
[HASS] Can you believe that
kaiju?
[BORR]
[MAX] Why is it kaiju keep
appearing around
[YUTA]
[MAX]
[MAX] It's no surprise, he's
tired.