[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SINCE THE GAME BEGAN,
A WHOLE MONTH HAS GONE BY, AND
2,000 PEOPLE HAVE DIED SO FAR.
AFTER ALL THIS TIME, NONE OF THE
PLAYERS HAVE BEEN ABLE TO CLEAR
FLOOR 1.
I USED TO BE A BETA TESTER, AND
EVEN I HAVEN'T FOUND OUT WHERE
THE BOSS'S LAIR IS.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
AND TODAY, FINALLY, WE'RE HAVING
A MEETING TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO
FIND AND DEFEAT THE FLOOR 1
BOSS.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: [ CLAPS ]
OKAY, PEOPLE.
NOW THAT EVERYONE'S HERE, LET'S
GET THIS MEETING STARTED.
SO, ANYWAY, I WANT TO THANK
EVERYONE FOR COMING.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
MY NAME IS DIABEL, AND IN THIS
GAME, THE JOB I ROLLED IS
KNIGHT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
&gt;&gt; DUDE, THERE'S NO JOB SYSTEM
IN THIS GAME.
&gt;&gt; KNIGHT.
&gt;&gt; Diabel: YOU GUYS WANT TO HEAR
THIS OR NOT?
[ LAUGHTER STOPS ]
RIGHT.
ANYWAY, HERE'S THE DEAL -- OUR
PARTY FOUND THE BOSS ROOM AT THE
TOP OF THE TOWER TODAY.
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
FIRST, WE NEED TO DEFEAT THE
BOSS AND MAKE IT TO FLOOR 2.
THE NEXT STEP IS WE HAVE TO TELL
EVERYONE WAITING IN
THE TOWN OF BEGINNINGS THAT IT
IS POSSIBLE TO BEAT THIS GAME.
FACT IS, IT'S OUR DUTY AS THE
MOST CAPABLE PLAYERS HERE.
DO YOU AGREE OR NOT?
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; [ WHISTLES ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: OKAY.
GLAD TO HEAR YOU'RE ALL WITH ME
ON THIS.
NOW LET'S FIGURE OUT HOW WE'RE
GONNA BEAT THE BOSS.
FIRST OFF, WE'LL TEAM UP INTO
PARTIES OF SIX.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: A TYPICAL PARTY
DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE AGAINST A
FLOOR BOSS.
WE NEED A RAID GROUP MADE UP OF
MULTIPLE PARTIES.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
YOU GOT LEFT OUT, TOO, HUH?
&gt;&gt; NOT EVEN.
I WASN'T LEFT OUT.
IT'S JUST EVERYONE SEEMS LIKE
THEY'RE ALREADY FRIENDS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO, YOU'RE SOLO, TOO?
YOU WANT TO FORM A PARTY WITH ME?
YOU HEARD WHAT THE GUY JUST
SAID.
WE CAN'T BEAT THE BOSS ON OUR
OWN.
AND IT WOULD ONLY BE FOR THIS
FIGHT.
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: ALL RIGHT!
LOOKS LIKE EVERYONE'S TEAMED UP.
NOW, THEN --
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: HOLD UP A SEC!
[ GRUNTING ]
MY NAME'S KEBAOU. GOT THAT?
BEFORE WE TAKE ON THE BOSS, I
WANT TO GET SOMETHING OFF MY
CHEST.
WE ALL KNOW ABOUT THE 2,000
PEOPLE WHO'VE DIED SO FAR, YEAH?
WELL, SOME OF YOU NEED TO
APOLOGIZE TO 'EM RIGHT NOW!
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: KEBAOU, I THINK I
KNOW WHO YOU'RE REFERRING TO.
YOU MEAN THE ONES WHO ARE
EX-BETA TESTERS, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: 'COURSE I MEAN THEM!
THE DAY THIS STUPID-ASS GAME
STARTED, THE BETA GUYS JUST UP
AND VANISHED, RIGHT?!
THEY DITCHED ALL US BEGINNERS!
THEY SNAGGED ALL THE GOOD
HUNTING SPOTS, AND THEY GRABBED
ALL THE EASY QUESTS, TOO.
THEY WERE THE ONLY ONES GETTING
STRONGER IN HERE.
THIS WHOLE TIME, THEY'VE IGNORED
US LIKE WE'RE NOTHING.
[ GROWLS ]
HELL, I BET THERE'S SOME OF THEM
HERE!
COME ON OUT, BETA TESTERS!
WE SHOULD MAKE THEM APOLOGIZE TO
US, AND WE SHOULD MAKE THEM ALL
GIVE UP THEIR MONEY AND THE
ITEMS THEY GOT.
THEY CAN'T EXPECT THE PARTY TO
TRUST THEM WHEN THEY DON'T TRUST US.
WHY SHOULD WE?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
&gt;&gt; CAN I SAY SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: HEY. MY NAME'S AGIL.
KEBAOU, RIGHT?
I WANT TO MAKE SURE I'M ON THE
SAME PAGE.
YOU SAY THE EX-BETA TESTERS
SHOULD BE BLAMED FOR THE
ROOKIES' DEATHS BECAUSE THEY
DIDN'T HELP THEM AND YOU WANT
THEM TO APOLOGIZE AND GIVE UP
THEIR WINNINGS.
I LEAVE ANYTHING OUT?
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: NO. YOU DIDN'T.
&gt;&gt; Agil: THE ITEM STORE HANDS
THESE OUT FOR FREE.
IT'S A GUIDE BOOK.
YOU GOT ONE, DIDN'T YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: SURE, I GOT ONE.
SO, WHAT ABOUT IT?
&gt;&gt; Agil: YOU KNOW WHO WAS
HANDING THESE OUT?
THE EX-BETA TESTERS.
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: LISTEN UP.
EVERYONE HAD EQUAL ACCESS TO
THIS INFORMATION.
EVEN SO, LOTS OF PLAYERS STILL
DIED.
NOW, I DIDN'T COME HERE TO POINT
FINGERS AT ANYONE.
I'M HERE 'CAUSE I WANT TO LEARN
FROM THOSE PLAYERS' DEATHS.
I'M HERE BECAUSE I WANT TO FIND
OUT HOW WE'RE GONNA BEAT THE
BOSS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: [ GROWLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: OKAY.
CAN WE GET BACK TO THE MEETING
NOW?
FOR INFO ON THE BOSS, IT'S ALL
IN HERE -- THE LATEST ISSUE OF
THE GUIDE BOOK YOU JUST HEARD
ABOUT.
&gt;&gt; All: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Diabel: ACCORDING TO THE
BOOK, THE BOSS'S NAME IS
ILLFANG THE KOBOLD LORD.
ALSO, HE'LL BE SURROUNDED
BY HIS MINIONS,
THE RUIN KOBOLD SENTINELS.
ILLFANG CARRIES AN AX AND A
BUCKLER.
HE HAS FOUR HEALTH BARS, AND
WHEN THE LAST ONE TURNS RED, HE
SWITCHES TO A CURVED SWORD-TYPE
WEAPON CALLED A TULWAR.
HE CAN CHANGE HIS PATTERNS OF
ATTACK, TOO.
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
THAT'S IT FOR THE BRIEFING.
AS FOR THE DISTRIBUTION OF LOOT,
MONEY WILL BE DIVIDED EQUALLY
AMONG EVERYONE.
THE PARTY THAT DEFEATS THE BOSS
GETS THE XP, AND WHOEVER GETS AN
ITEM GETS TO KEEP IT.
ANY OBJECTIONS?
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
GOOD!
WE LEAVE TOMORROW AT 10:00 IN
THE MORNING.
MEETING ADJOURNED, PEOPLE!
[ MURMURING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THOSE ARE PRETTY
GOOD, AREN'T THEY?
MIND IF I SIT DOWN?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU REALLY THINK THESE
TASTE GOOD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
SINCE I CAME TO THIS TOWN, I END
UP EATING AT LEAST ONE A DAY.
'COURSE, I GOT A TRICK TO MAKE
IT TASTE BETTER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT TRICK?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: TRY IT WITH SOME OF
THAT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
CREAM.
[ MUNCHES ]
[ MUNCHING ]
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I GOT IT FROM
"THE HEIFER STRIKES BACK."
THAT'S THE QUEST IN THE VILLAGE
BEFORE YOU GET TO THIS ONE.
YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW I DID IT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MNH-MNH.
I APPRECIATE THE OFFER, BUT I
DIDN'T COME TO THIS TOWN TO EAT
GOOD FOOD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO I DON'T LOSE SIGHT
OF WHO I AM.
I DON'T WANT TO LOCK MYSELF IN A
ROOM IN THE TOWN OF BEGINNINGS
AND SLOWLY ROT AWAY.
I'D RATHER STAY THE WAY I AM
TILL THE LAST MOMENT...
EVEN IF A MONSTER BEATS ME AND I
DIE.
I WON'T LOSE -- TO THIS GAME OR
THIS WORLD, NO MATTER WHAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHOMPS ]
I WOULDN'T WANT A PARTY MEMBER
DYING ON ME, SO TRY NOT TO DIE
TOMORROW.
LET'S GO OVER IT AGAIN.
WE'RE THE BACKUP, SO OUR
TARGET'S GONNA BE
THE BOSS'S MINIONS,
THE RUIN KOBOLD SENTINELS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I KNOW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL USE A SWORD
SKILL TO KNOCK THEIR WEAPONS UP
AND OUT OF THE WAY.
WHEN I DO, SWITCH AND JUMP IN.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT'S A SWITCH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, LEVEL WITH ME.
IS THIS THE FIRST TIME YOU'VE
EVER BEEN IN A PARTY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH-HUH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
I'VE ONLY GOT ONE THING TO SAY
TO YOU -- LET'S WIN!
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: COME ON!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
[ ROARS ]
[ ALL ROAR ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: COMMENCE ATTACK!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: SQUADS "A" AND "C,"
SWITCH IN!
HERE IT COMES!
SQUAD "B," BLOCK!
SQUAD "C," KEEP GUARDING AND
PREPARE TO SWITCH.
EVERYONE ELSE, WHEN YOU FALL
BACK, REGROUP AND FLANK THEM.
SQUADS "D," "E," AND "F," KEEP
THOSE MINIONS OFF US!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, YOU GOT IT!
SWITCH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M ON IT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] I
THOUGHT SHE WAS A BEGINNER, BUT
SHE'S GOT GOOD SKILLS.
I CAN'T EVEN SEE THE TIP OF HER
SWORD.
[ GRUNTS SOFTLY ] RIGHT ON.
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
[ GROWLING ]
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: LOOKS LIKE THE GUIDE
BOOK WAS RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; Diabel: STAND BACK!
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Diabel: I GOT IT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
[ Thinking ] I THOUGHT THE PLAN
WAS FOR EVERYONE IN THE GROUP TO
SURROUND IT.
[ GASPS ]
THAT'S NOT A TULWAR.
IT'S A NODACHI!
THIS ISN'T LIKE THE BETA!
[ GRUNTS ]
WAIT! STOP!
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S NO GOOD!
GET OUT OF THERE!
&gt;&gt; Diabel: AAAH!
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: DIABEL, NO!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DIABEL!
&gt;&gt; Diabel: [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT THE HELL WERE
YOU THINKING?
&gt;&gt; Diabel: [ GRUNTS ]
YOU KNOW...YOU WERE A BETA
TESTER, TOO, WEREN'T YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Diabel: YOU WERE AFTER THE
LAST ATTACK BONUS -- THE RARE
ITEM.
YOU'RE JUST LIKE ME -- A BETA
TESTER.
[ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
PLEASE, YOU HAVE TO...DEFEAT THE
BOSS...
FOR EVERYONE HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
WHEN THIS DEATH GAME STARTED,
THE ONLY THING I THOUGHT ABOUT
WAS HOW I WAS GONNA SURVIVE.
NOTHING ELSE MATTERED.
TAKE CARE.
I'LL BE SEEING YOU, KLEIN.
BUT YOU WEREN'T LIKE THAT,
DIABEL.
YOU NEVER ABANDONED THE OTHER
PLAYERS.
YOU BROUGHT THEM TOGETHER.
YOU LED EVERYONE, AND YOU FOUGHT
BRILLIANTLY.
YOU TRIED TO ACCOMPLISH
SOMETHING I COULDN'T.
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'LL GO, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
WE'LL HIT 'EM JUST LIKE WE DID
THE MINIONS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU GOT IT.
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SWITCH!
ASUNA!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
HYAH!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HE'S COMING BACK!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YAH! UGH! UGH!
OH, NO.
AAH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLING ]
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: WE CAN HOLD THIS
BASTARD OFF UNTIL YOUR HEALTH'S
BACK UP.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU GOT IT.
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WATCH OUT!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
COME ON, ASUNA!
HELP ME BEAT THIS SUCKER!
ONE LAST ATTACK!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU GOT IT!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
[ BOTH SHOUT ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
[ OPERATIC SINGING ]
&gt;&gt; UH...
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
&gt;&gt; YEAH!
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT!
COME ON, BABY!
&gt;&gt; WHOO! YES! COME ON!
THEY AIN'T GOT NOTHIN' ON US!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NICE JOB.
&gt;&gt; Agil: THAT WAS SOME FINE
SWORDSMANSHIP.
CONGRATULATIONS.
TODAY'S VICTORY IS ALL THANKS
TO YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO.
&gt;&gt; YEAH! YOU ROCK, MAN!
[ SCATTERED CHEERS AND
APPLAUSE ]
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: STOP CHEERING!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE STOP ]
WHY'D YOU DO IT, HUH?
WHY'D YOU LET DIABEL DIE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LET HIM DIE?
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: UGH!
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
ADMIT IT -- YOU KNEW THE
TECHNIQUE THE BOSS WAS GONNA
USE.
YOU COULD'VE TOLD US!
THEN DIABEL WOULD'VE STOOD A
CHANCE.
HE WOULDN'T HAVE HAD TO DIE!
[ ALL MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; I KNOW WHY HE KNEW!
HE USED TO BE A BETA TESTER!
THINK ABOUT IT!
HE KNEW THE BOSS'S ATTACK
PATTERNS.
HE KNEW, BUT HE KEPT IT FROM US!
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: [ SNIFFLES ]
&gt;&gt; AND I BET HE'S NOT THE ONLY
BETA TESTER HERE.
COME ON! SHOW YOURSELVES!
[ ALL MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] THIS IS
BAD.
AT THIS RATE...
&gt;&gt; Diabel: ...FOR EVERYONE HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
[ GULPS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: HEY, CALM DOWN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ LAUGHING ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: HMM?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ LAUGHING
CONTINUES ]
SO, YOU GUYS THINK I USED TO BE
A BETA TESTER.
IT'S NOT COOL TO PUT ME IN THE
SAME CLASS WITH THOSE NOOBS.
&gt;&gt; WHAT'D YOU SAY?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU HEARD ME.
MOST OF THE THOUSAND PEOPLE WHO
SCORED A SLOT IN "S.A.O.'s" BETA
WERE ROOKIES.
THEY WERE SO GREEN, THEY DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW HOW TO LEVEL UP.
HELL, EVEN YOU GUYS ARE BETTER
THAN THEY WERE.
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT ME -- I'M NOTHING
LIKE THOSE GUYS, MAN.
DURING THE BETA, I MADE IT TO
FLOORS THAT WERE HIGHER THAN ANY
OF THE OTHER TESTERS.
THAT'S A FACT.
I KNEW ABOUT THE BOSS 'CAUSE I
FOUGHT TONS OF MONSTERS WITH WAY
MORE SWORD SKILLS ON HIGHER
FLOORS.
I KNOW A BUNCH OF OTHER THINGS,
TOO -- MORE THAN YOU CAN
IMAGINE, MORE THAN ANY INFO
BROKER.
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: WH-WHAT THE HELL?
IF THAT'S TRUE, THEN YOU'RE
WORSE THAN A BETA TESTER.
YOU'RE A [BLEEP] CHEATER!
THAT'S WHAT YOU ARE!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; HE'S A BETA TESTER AND A
CHEATER!
HE'S A BEATER!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: A BEATER.
YEAH, THAT'S GOOD. I LIKE IT.
&gt;&gt; Kebaou: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
YOU CAN CALL ME A BEATER.
JUST BE SURE YOU DON'T CONFUSE
ME WITH THOSE BETA TESTERS
ANYMORE.
[ BEEPS ]
[ STATIC ]
[ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WAIT.
WHEN WE WERE FIGHTING THE BOSS,
YOU CALLED ME BY MY NAME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I WASN'T TRYING TO BE
RUDE.
DID I MESS UP THE PRONUNCIATION?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HOW'D YOU EVEN
KNOW IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF YOU LOOK RIGHT
ABOUT HERE, YOU'LL SEE ANOTHER
HP GAUGE UNDER YOURS.
THERE'S A NAME WRITTEN RIGHT
NEXT TO IT, YEAH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
KIRITO.
KIRITO?
YOUR NAME'S KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
[ LAUGHS ]
I'M SO DUMB.
IT WAS THERE THE WHOLE TIME, AND
I NEVER KNEW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU CAN BECOME
POWERFUL HERE ON YOUR OWN, BUT
IF THE DAY COMES WHEN SOMEONE
YOU TRUST INVITES YOU TO JOIN A
GUILD, DON'T TURN IT DOWN,
'CAUSE THERE ARE LIMITS TO WHAT
A SOLO PLAYER CAN DO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BUT YOU'RE SOLO.
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]