[ OPERATIC SINGING ]
&gt;&gt; HI, THERE!
TIME FOR THIS WEEK'S MMO STREAM.
YOU JUST SAW A PROMO OF TODAY'S
FEATURED GAME, AND THIS IS WHAT
LAST WEEK'S LAUNCH DAY LOOKED
LIKE.
CAN YOU GUESS WHAT EVERYONE'S
WAITING IN LINE FOR?
"SWORD ART ONLINE"!
THE FIRST PERSON IN LINE SAID
THEY CAMPED OUT FOR THREE DAYS.
BUT, HEY, IF YOU'RE A HARD-CORE
GAMER, THAT'S WHAT YOU DO.
ON TODAY'S EPISODE OF THE MMO
STREAM, WE'LL BE COVERING THE
INTERNATIONALLY FAMOUS
"SWORD ART ONLINE," A.K.A.
"S.A.O."!
UP TO NOW, NONE OF THE NerveGear
SOFTWARE WE'VE SEEN HAS TAKEN
ADVANTAGE OF THE POSSIBILITIES
OF THE HARDWARE.
&gt;&gt; Suguha: HEY!
I'M OFF TO PRACTICE NOW!
SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; BUT "S.A.O." WAS MADE BY THE
INVENTOR OF NerveGear,
AKIHIKO KAYABA.
HECK, THIS IS THE VR MMORPG THAT
ME AND EVERYONE ELSE HAVE BEEN
WAITING FOR!
THE BETA TESTERS SAY IT'S
INCREDIBLE!
I WISH I COULD HAVE GOTTEN ONE!
THE FIRST PRESSING WAS LIMITED
TO ONLY 10,000 COPIES.
THOSE FANS IN LINE SNAPPED THEM
UP, AND ONLINE, THE GAME SOLD
OUT IN SECONDS.
[ BEEPING, WHIRRING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
[ BEEPING AND WHIRRING
CONTINUE ]
LINK START!
[ HEART BEATING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
HELLO, WORLD.
I'M BACK.
[ PEOPLE CHEERING ]
&gt;&gt; WELL, I TOLD HIM, SO IT'S HIS
DEAL.
&gt;&gt; WHY DON'T WE FORM A PARTY?
&gt;&gt; WELL, I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE.
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON. IT'LL BE GREAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: HUH?
HEY, BRO! WAIT UP!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S UP?
&gt;&gt; Klein: HOO!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
YOU ACT LIKE YOU KNOW YOUR WAY
AROUND HERE.
YOU WERE IN THE BETA TEST,
WEREN'T YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, YEAH.
&gt;&gt; Klein: COOL.
TODAY'S MY FIRST DAY.
SO, COULD YOU GIVE ME SOME TIPS
ON THE LOWER FLOORS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I DON'T
KNOW IF --
&gt;&gt; Klein: OH, PLEASE?!
I'M BEGGING YOU!
LOOK, MY NAME'S KLEIN.
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
ALL RIGHT. I'M KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Klein: AAAAAAH!
UGH!
KILL ME NOW!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, COME ON.
SERIOUSLY?
&gt;&gt; Klein: OHH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU CAN'T FEEL ANY
PAIN.
&gt;&gt; Klein: UH? OH, YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT. SORRY. HABIT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: REMEMBER WHAT I SAID?
THE FIRST MOVE IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT.
&gt;&gt; Klein: YEAH, THAT'S EASY FOR
YOU TO SAY.
BUT HE WON'T STAND STILL.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF YOU DO YOUR
INITIAL MOTION RIGHT AND ACTIVE
A SWORD SKILL AT THE RIGHT
TIME...
&gt;&gt; [ SQUEALS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ...THE SYSTEM PRETTY
MUCH GUARANTEES YOU'LL ALWAYS
HIT YOUR TARGET.
&gt;&gt; Klein: INITIAL MOTION?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HERE'S AN EASIER WAY
TO LOOK AT IT.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
RIGHT AFTER YOU START YOUR MOVE,
WAIT FOR A LITTLE BIT.
WHEN YOU FEEL THE SKILL START TO
ACTIVATE, DRIVE IT HOME.
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ SIGHS ]
DRIVE IT HOME?
[ SIGHS ]
HYAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ CHUCKLES ]
HOO HOO!
YE-E-E-E-E-E-AH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CONGRATULATIONS.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HMM?
HA HA!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT WAS NICE.
BUT THAT BOAR'S ABOUT AS WEAK AS
SLIMES IN OTHER GAMES ARE.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HOLY CRAP!
YOU GOT BE KIDDING!
I THOUGHT THAT THING WAS A
MID-LEVEL BOSS!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH, AS IF.
[ BOARS GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: WHOA!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ADDICTIVE, ISN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; Klein: I'LL SAY.
[ GRUNTS ]
SO, THESE SKILLS -- THERE'S A
TON OF THEM, LIKE BLACKSMITHING
AND STUFF, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I HEARD THE GAME HAS
AN UNLIMITED NUMBER OF THEM, ALL
EXCEPT FOR MAGIC, THOUGH.
&gt;&gt; Klein: AN RPG WITHOUT MAGIC?
THAT'S BOLD DECISION, MAN.
[ Laughing ] OH, YEAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO, WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
IT'S KIND OF FUN TO MOVE YOUR
BODY AS YOU FIGHT, ISN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; Klein: HA HA!
OH, HELLS, YEAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU READY TO MOVE ON?
&gt;&gt; Klein: YEAH, MAN!
LET'S KEEP GOING.
[ BIRDS SQUAWKING ]
WHEN I LOOK AROUND, I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT.
WE'RE INSIDE A GAME, BRO!
WHOEVER MADE IT'S A GENIUS.
THIS THING'S AMAZING.
MAKES ME GLAD I WAS BORN WHEN I
WAS, YOU KNOW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S NOT THAT BIG A
DEAL.
&gt;&gt; Klein: CUT ME SOME SLACK.
IT'S MY FIRST FULL DIVE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU NEVER USED
NerveGear BEFORE TODAY, HUH?
THIS IS YOUR FIRST TIME EVER?
&gt;&gt; Klein: UH-HUH.
AS SOON AS I GOT THE MONEY
TOGETHER, I RUSHED OUT AND
BOUGHT ALL THE HARDWARE TO PLAY
"S.A.O."
STOOD IN LINE AND SCORED ONE OF
THE 10,000 HARD COPIES.
GUESS YOU COULD SAY I WAS PRETTY
LUCKY, ALTHOUGH YOU, SIR, WERE
10 TIMES AS LUCKY GETTING TO
BETA-TEST IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM?
&gt;&gt; Klein: DUDE, ONLY A THOUSAND
PEOPLE GOT THE CHANCE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I GUESS I WAS
LUCKY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HEY, MIND IF I ASK HOW
FAR YOU GOT IN THE BETA?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EH, TWO MONTHS AND I
COULDN'T GET FURTHER THAN
FLOOR 8.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HMM?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT NOW I THINK I CAN
GET THERE WITHIN A MONTH, EASY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
YOU'RE REALLY INTO THIS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, YOU COULD SAY
THAT.
DURING THE BETA TEST, "S.A.O."
WAS THE ONLY THING ON MY MIND,
DAY AND NIGHT.
IN THIS WORLD, A SINGLE BLADE
CAN TAKE YOU ANYWHERE YOU WANT
TO GO.
AND EVEN THOUGH IT'S A VIRTUAL
WORLD, I FEEL MORE ALIVE IN HERE
THAN I EVER DID IN THE REAL ONE.
[ SCOFFS ]
ANYWAY, YOU WANT TO GO DO SOME
MORE HUNTING?
&gt;&gt; Klein: OH, YOU KNOW IT.
BUT THE THING IS...
[ STOMACH GROWLS ]
...I'M REALLY HUNGRY.
I HAVE TO LOG OUT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: TOO BAD THE FOOD YOU
EAT HERE ONLY SATISFIES YOUR
HUNGER VIRTUALLY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: YEAH, FOR REALS.
THAT'S WHY I ORDERED A PIZZA
FOR 5:30.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WOW.
YOU'RE SO PREPARED.
&gt;&gt; Klein: YOU KNOW IT.
BESIDES, THE GAME CAN WAIT UNTIL
I GET MY PIZZA ON.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I GUESS.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HEY, I WAS GONNA GO
MEET UP WITH SOME PEOPLE I KNOW
FROM ANOTHER GAME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE UP TO
AFTER THIS, SO, YOU KNOW, IF YOU
WANT, YOU CAN FRIEND THEM AND
HANG WITH US.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...MNH.
&gt;&gt; Klein: NO.
IT'S COOL IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
NO PRESSURE.
I CAN ALWAYS INTRODUCE YOU TO
THEM ANOTHER TIME OR SOMETHING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. SORRY.
THANKS ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: NO WAY.
I SHOULD BE DOING ALL THE
THANKING.
HEY, ONE OF THESE DAYS, I
PROMISE I'LL PAY YOU BACK FOR
ALL YOUR HELP -- VIRTUALLY, THAT
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; Klein: THANKS FOR EVERYTHING,
MAN, REALLY.
GUESS I'LL SEE YOU AROUND, THEN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF THERE'S ANYTHING
ELSE YOU WANT TO KNOW,
MESSAGE ME.
&gt;&gt; Klein: SWEET! I'LL DO THAT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ BEEPING ]
HUH?
WHERE'D THE LOGOUT BUTTON GO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT SHOULD BE THERE.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HMM.
NO, IT'S NOT THERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT SHOULD BE AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE MAIN MENU.
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: SEE? NOT THERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S NOT.
&gt;&gt; Klein: OH, WELL.
TODAY'S, WHAT, THE FIRST DAY OUT
OF BETA?
THERE'S BOUND TO BE SOME BUGS.
I BET THE SERVER PEOPLE ARE
FREAKING OUT RIGHT NOW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU WILL, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LOOK. IT'S 5:25.
&gt;&gt; Klein: AAH! OH, MY GOD!
MY TERIYAKI MAYO PIZZA AND
GINGER ALE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY DON'T YOU JUST
CONTACT THE GAME MASTER?
&gt;&gt; Klein: HUH?
YEAH, I DID THAT, BUT NOTHING'S
HAPPENING.
HE'S NOT PICKING UP.
DO YOU KNOW IF THERE'S ANOTHER
WAY TO LOG OUT OF THIS THING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
WHENEVER A PLAYER WANTS TO LOG
OUT OF "S.A.O.," THE ONLY WAY
THEY CAN DO IT IS BY GOING
THROUGH THE MENU.
&gt;&gt; Klein: THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME OTHER
WAY OUT.
RETURN! LOG OUT! ESCAPE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: TOLD YOU SO.
AND THERE WAS NO EMERGENCY
LOGOUT IN THE MANUAL, EITHER.
&gt;&gt; Klein: NO WAY.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
I KNOW -- I'LL JUST RIP THE
NerveGear OFF MY HEAD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T BOTHER.
ONCE YOU'RE HOOKED IN, YOU CAN'T
MOVE YOUR BODY IN THE REAL WORLD
ANYMORE.
THE NerveGear INTERCEPTS ALL THE
COMMANDS YOU GIVE FROM INSIDE
THE GAME USING AN INTERFACE
BUILT INTO THE RIG.
&gt;&gt; Klein: SERIOUSLY?
SO, NOW WE GOT TO WAIT UNTIL
SOMEONE GETS AROUND TO FIXING
THE BUG?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT OR UNTIL SOMEONE
IN THE REAL WORLD COMES ALONG
AND TAKES THE NerveGear OFF US.
THAT'S IT.
&gt;&gt; Klein: WELL, I LIVE ALONE.
YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I GOT A MOM AND A
SISTER, AND I'M PRETTY SURE
THEY'LL NOTICE BY DINNERTIME AND
COME LOOKING --
&gt;&gt; Klein: YOU GOT A SISTER?
HOW OLD IS SHE? WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SHE'S INTO SPORTS AND
HATES GAMES, AND SHE'S TOTALLY
NOT YOUR TYPE, MAN.
SHE WOULDN'T DATE A GAMER IF
HE'S THE LAST GUY --
&gt;&gt; Klein: WHO CARES?
I WANT TO -- OHH-OHH!
AHH! OHH! OHH! MNH! GAH!
OH, RIGHT -- GETTING KICKED IN
THE BALLS DOESN'T HURT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GET SERIOUS.
DON'T YOU THINK THIS IS WEIRD?
&gt;&gt; Klein: YEAH, TOTALLY, BUT
IT'S JUST A BUG.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THIS ISN'T JUST A
BUG.
IF WE CAN'T LOG OUT, IT'S GONNA
CAUSE SOME SERIOUS PROBLEMS FOR
THE GAME.
&gt;&gt; Klein: YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE
RIGHT.
I WONDER IF THE DEVELOPERS EVEN
KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING, 'CAUSE
THEY COULD JUST SHUT DOWN THE
SERVER AND LOG EVERYONE OUT.
BUT WHY HAVEN'T THEY MADE AN
ANNOUNCEMENT?
&gt;&gt; Klein: UH...HMM.
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ RINGING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SHUDDERS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON?
&gt;&gt; UNH-UNH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SOMEONE FORCED A
TELEPORT.
[ RINGING STOPS ]
[ CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S GOING ON?
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LOOK -- UP THERE.
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ GASPS ]
[ ALARM BLARING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOW WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Klein: WHAT THE HELL IS THAT
THING?
&gt;&gt; IS THAT THE GAME MASTER?
&gt;&gt; WHY DOESN'T HE HAVE A FACE?
&gt;&gt; IS THIS AN EVENT?
&gt;&gt; I'M SCARED.
&gt;&gt; DON'T WORRY.
IT'S JUST PART OF THE OPENING
CEREMONY.
&gt;&gt; ATTENTION, PLAYERS.
I WELCOME YOU TO MY WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S HE MEAN BY
THAT?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: MY NAME IS
AKIHIKO KAYABA, AND AS OF THIS
MOMENT, I AM IN CONTROL OF THIS
WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; SERIOUSLY?
&gt;&gt; IS THAT REALLY HIM?
&gt;&gt; WOW. THAT'S SOME ENTRANCE.
&gt;&gt; I'M SURE MOST OF YOU HAVE
ALREADY NOTICED AN ITEM MISSING
FROM YOUR MAIN MENUS -- THE
LOGOUT BUTTON.
LET ME ASSURE YOU THIS IS NOT A
DEFECT IN THE GAME.
I REPEAT, THIS IS NOT A DEFECT.
THIS IS HOW "SWORD ART ONLINE"
WAS DESIGNED TO BE.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HE'S KIDDING, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; YOU CANNOT LOG YOURSELVES OUT
OF "S.A.O.," AND NO ONE OUTSIDE
WILL BE ABLE TO SHUT DOWN OR
REMOVE THE NerveGear FROM YOUR
HEAD.
IF ANYONE ATTEMPTS TO DO SO, A
TRANSMITTER INSIDE THE NerveGear
WILL DISCHARGE A MICROWAVE
SIGNAL INTO YOUR SKULL,
DESTROYING YOUR BRAIN AND ENDING
YOUR LIFE.
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
&gt;&gt; COME ON! THAT'S SUCH B.S.
&gt;&gt; LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
&gt;&gt; UGH! HEY, I CAN'T GET OUT!
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ CHUCKLES ]
ARE YOU LISTENING TO THIS CRAP?
HE'S GOT TO BE NUTS, RIGHT?
RIGHT, KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HE'S NOT.
THE TRANSMITTER SIGNALS IN THE
HEADGEAR WORK JUST LIKE
MICROWAVES.
IF THE SAFETY'S DISABLED, IT
COULD FRY YOUR BRAIN.
&gt;&gt; Klein: COULDN'T SOMEONE CUT
THE POWER OR...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT WON'T WORK.
THE NerveGear'S GOT AN INTERNAL
BATTERY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: UGH! UGH!
THIS IS CRAZY!
IT'S TOTALLY CRAZY!
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: DESPITE MY WARNING,
THE FAMILIES AND FRIENDS OF SOME
OF THE PLAYERS HAVE ATTEMPTED
REMOVING THE NerveGear, AN
UNFORTUNATE DECISION, TO SAY THE
LEAST.
AS A RESULT, THE GAME NOW HAS
213 LESS PLAYERS THAN WHEN IT
BEGAN.
THEY'VE BEEN DELETED FROM BOTH
AINCRAD AND THE REAL WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: 213?
&gt;&gt; Klein: NO WAY.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: AS YOU CAN SEE,
INTERNATIONAL MEDIA OUTLETS HAVE
'ROUND-THE-CLOCK COVERAGE OF
EVERYTHING, INCLUDING THE
DEATHS.
AT THIS POINT, IT'S SAFE TO
ASSUME THE LIKELIHOOD OF A
NerveGear BEING REMOVED IS
MINIMAL, AT BEST.
I HOPE THIS BRINGS YOU A LITTLE
COMFORT AS YOU TRY TO CLEAR THE
GAME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: IT'S IMPORTANT TO
REMEMBER THE FOLLOWING -- THERE
IS NO LONGER ANY WAY TO REVIVE
SOMEONE WITHIN THE GAME.
IF YOUR H.P. DROPS TO ZERO, YOUR
AVATAR WILL BE DELETED FROM THE
SYSTEM FOREVER.
AND THE NerveGear WILL
SIMULTANEOUSLY DESTROY YOUR
BRAIN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
FOR A PLAYER TO ESCAPE NOW.
YOU MUST CLEAR THE GAME.
RIGHT NOW YOU'RE GATHERED ON
FLOOR 1, THE LOWEST LEVEL OF
AINCRAD.
IF YOU CAN GET THROUGH THE
DUNGEON AND DEFEAT THE BOSS, YOU
MAY ADVANCE TO THE NEXT FLOOR.
DEFEAT THE BOSS ON FLOOR 100,
AND YOU WILL CLEAR THE GAME.
&gt;&gt; CLEAR?
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
&gt;&gt; WHAT?
&gt;&gt; WHY SHOULD WE BELIEVE ANY OF
THE CRAP YOU'RE SAYING?!
&gt;&gt; Klein: WE CAN'T CLEAR ALL 100
FLOORS.
THAT'S FREAKING IMPOSSIBLE.
EVEN THE BETA TESTERS NEVER MADE
IT THAT HIGH!
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: LAST BUT NOT LEAST,
I'VE PLACED A LITTLE PRESENT IN
THE ITEM STORAGE OF EVERY
PLAYER.
PLEASE HAVE A LOOK.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
A MIRROR?
&gt;&gt; COIN!
[ PEOPLE GASPING AND SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UGH!
&gt;&gt; Klein: YOU OKAY, KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. WAIT.
WHO ARE YOU?
&gt;&gt; Klein: I'M ME. WHO ARE YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ ALL MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; SON OF A -- YOU'RE A GUY?!
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE NOT 17!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAIT A SECOND.
IS THAT YOU, KLEIN?
&gt;&gt; Klein: IS THAT YOU, KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Klein: BUT HOW...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THE SCAN.
THERE'S A HIGH-DENSITY SIGNAL
DEVICE INSIDE THE NerveGear RIG.
IT CAN SEE WHAT MY FACE LOOKS
LIKE.
BUT HOW'S IT KNOW MY HEIGHT AND
BODY TYPE?
&gt;&gt; Klein: WHEN YOU FIRST PUT THE
NerveGear ON, IT HAD YOU DO THIS
CALIBRATION THING.
IT ASKED YOU TO TOUCH YOUR BODY
ALL OVER LIKE THIS, REMEMBER?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S WHERE IT GOT OUR PHYSICAL
DATA.
&gt;&gt; Klein: BUT THIS IS -- WHAT'S
THE POINT?
WHY WOULD ANYONE DO THIS TO US?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I THINK HE'S ABOUT TO
TELL US.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: RIGHT NOW, YOU'RE
PROBABLY WONDERING WHY.
WHY WOULD AKIHIKO KAYABA,
DEVELOPER OF "SWORD ART ONLINE"
AND NerveGear, DO THIS?
ULTIMATELY, MY GOAL WAS A SIMPLE
ONE.
THE REASON I CREATED
"SWORD ART ONLINE" WAS TO
CONTROL THE FATE OF A WORLD OF
MY DESIGN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: KAYABA.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: AS YOU CAN SEE, I
HAVE ACHIEVED MY GOAL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: THIS MARKS THE END
OF THE TUTORIAL AND THE OFFICIAL
LAUNCH OF "SWORD ART ONLINE."
PLAYERS, I WISH YOU THE BEST OF
LUCK.
[ STATIC, BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S NOT A GAME.
IT'S REAL.
AKIHIKO KAYABA CREATED A VIRTUAL
WORLD.
HE DESIGNED THE NerveGear RIG.
THE MAN'S A GENIUS.
I'VE BEEN A FAN OF HIS FOR A
LONG TIME, SO I KNOW EVERYTHING
HE JUST SAID IS THE TRUTH.
IF I DIE IN THE GAME, I'LL DIE
IN REAL LIFE.
&gt;&gt; MY GOD! NO!
[ ALL GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; LET ME OUT!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T STAY HERE!
I HAVE A MEETING AFTER THIS!
&gt;&gt; STOP PUSHING!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE TO LET US GO!
&gt;&gt; WAIT, SERIOUSLY?!
&gt;&gt; WHAT DID WE EVER DO TO YOU?
WE JUST WANTED TO PLAY A GAME!
COME BACK!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME ON, KLEIN.
&gt;&gt; Klein: AAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, LISTEN -- I'M
HEADING OUT RIGHT NOW FOR THE
NEXT VILLAGE.
I WANT YOU TO COME.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF WHAT HE SAID IS
TRUE -- AND I THINK IT IS -- THE
ONLY WAY WE'RE GONNA SURVIVE IN
HERE IS BY MAKING OURSELVES AS
STRONG AS POSSIBLE.
IN AN MMORPG, THE MONEY YOU CAN
EARN -- THE XP -- ONCE THE GAME
STARTS UP, THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH
OF THAT STUFF TO GO AROUND.
LOOK. THE FIELDS AROUND
THE TOWN OF BEGINNINGS ARE GONNA
BE HUNTED CLEAN SOON.
IF WE HEAD TO THE NEXT VILLAGE
NOW, WE'LL HAVE AN EASIER TIME
COLLECTING CASH AND POINTS.
DON'T WORRY.
I KNOW ALL THE PATHS AND PLACES
WE SHOULD AVOID.
EVEN IF I'M LEVEL 1, I CAN GET
THERE EASY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: WELL, THANKS, BUT YOU
KNOW THOSE FRIENDS OF MINE I WAS
TELLING YOU ABOUT?
WE STOOD IN LINE FOR A WHOLE
NIGHT TO BUY THIS, AND [SIGHS]
THEY'RE BACK AT THE PLAZA
SOMEWHERE.
AND I CAN'T LEAVE 'EM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] IF IT
WERE JUST KLEIN, BUT TWO MORE OR
EVEN ONE MORE --
&gt;&gt; Klein: SORRY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: CAN'T ASK A GUY I JUST
MET TO RISK HIS LIFE FOR A BUNCH
OF STRANGERS, CAN I?
SO DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
GET YOUR ASS TO THE NEXT
VILLAGE.
I'LL BE FINE.
LAST GAME I PLAYED, I RAN A
GUILD, SO I'M MORE THAN
PREPARED.
AND WITH ALL THE STUFF YOU
TAUGHT ME, I'LL GET BY, NO
SWEAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT, I'LL
GET GOING.
BUT IF YOU'RE IN A JAM, MESSAGE
ME, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Klein: SURE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL BE SEEING YOU,
KLEIN.
TAKE CARE.
&gt;&gt; Klein: KIRITO!
I...
HEY, KIRITO.
UH...YOU LOOK BETTER LIKE
THIS -- WAY COOLER THAN YOUR
AVATAR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, AND I THINK
THAT SCRUFFY FACE FITS YOU 10
TIMES BETTER, TOO.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
I GOT THIS. I CAN DO THIS.
THIS WORLD CAN'T BEAT ME.
AAAAH!
[ OPERATIC SINGING ]
I WILL SURVIVE.
[ GRUNTS ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]