>>I WANT TO SEE WHAT VIRTUAL
REALITY'S LIKE.
I WONDER WHEN I FIRST THOUGHT
THAT.
I USED TO HATE VIRTUAL-REALITY
GAMES WITH A VENGEANCE, AND I
BLAMED THEM FOR STEALING MY
BROTHER AWAY FROM ME.
BUT LATER ON, I GOT CURIOUS.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHY MY BROTHER
LOVED THEM SO MUCH, SO I
FIGURED, MAYBE I SHOULD SEE WHY
FOR MYSELF.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO EXPECT AT
FIRST, BUT AFTER A WHILE, I WAS
SURPRISED BY HOW MUCH I LOVED
ALFHEIM ONLINE.
[ GIGGLES ]
IT WAS AMAZING -- FLYING
THROUGH THE SKY ON MY VERY OWN
WINGS, TO FLY AS FAR AS I
WANTED, AS HIGH AS I WANTED,
AS FAST AS I WANTED.
I'D GIVE ANYTHING AND
EVERYTHING FOR THAT.
[ LAUGHS ]
I THINK I GET IT NOW.
I CAN SEE WHY MY BROTHER LOVES
THE VIRTUAL WORLD.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ BELLS TOLLING ]
&gt;&gt; HOLD IT, LEAFA!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ SIGHS ]
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU NOT TO CALL
ME THAT AT SCHOOL, NAGATA.
DIDN'T I?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, YOU DID.
SORRY, SUGUHA.
&gt;&gt; IDIOT!
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY!
I MEANT "KIRIGAYA"!
&gt;&gt; WHAT DO YOU WANT?
&gt;&gt; UH...
&gt;&gt; WAIT -- WHY ARE YOU EVEN
HERE?
YOU GOT A RELEASE FROM TAKING
THE HIGH-SCHOOL ENTRANCE EXAMS.
THEY'RE NOT MAKING YOU COME
ANYWAY, ARE THEY?
&gt;&gt; SUGU--
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; KIRIGAYA!
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU, SO I'VE
BEEN WAITING ALL MORNING.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; WAIT -- YOU'RE NOT HERE FOR
THE EXAMS, ARE YOU?
&gt;&gt; NO.
THE ADVISOR FOR THE KENDO CLUB
ASKED ME TO COME IN, THAT'S ALL.
WELL, WHAT'S UP?
&gt;&gt; IT'S SIGURD AND THE OTHERS.
THEY ALL WANTED TO GO HUNTING
AGAIN THIS AFTERNOON.
&gt;&gt; SORRY.
I WON'T BE GOING OUT WITH THOSE
GUYS FOR A WHILE.
&gt;&gt; WAIT! WHAT?!
WHY NOT?!
&gt;&gt; I'VE GOT PLANS TO HEAD OVER
TO ARUN.
THAT'S WHY.
&gt;&gt; BUT ISN'T ARUN AT THE BASE OF
THE WORLD TREE?
WAIT A SECOND!
YOU -- ARE YOU -- YOU'RE NOT
GOING WITH THAT SPRIGGAN?!
&gt;&gt; YEAH...
WELL...SORT OF.
I PROMISED I'D SHOW HIM HOW TO
GET THERE.
&gt;&gt; BUT...HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE DOING, LEA--
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERS ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
...K-KIRIGAYA?
IT'S JUST SO FAR AWAY, AND YOU
GUYS WILL BE...SLEEPING
TOGETHER, AND --
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
DON'T GET ANY WEIRD IDEAS ABOUT
IT, YOU JERK!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
[ GROANS ]
&gt;&gt; LOOK, I'VE MADE UP MY MIND,
AND THAT'S THAT.
SAY "HEY" TO SIGURD AND THE
OTHERS FOR ME.
SEE YA LATER!
ALL I'M DOING IS SHOWING HIM THE
WAY.
THAT'S ALL I'M DOING.
[ GROANS ]
[ BEEP ]
[ STEADY BEEPING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
LINK, START!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, THERE.
BEEN WAITING LONG?
&gt;&gt; NOT AT ALL. I JUST WALKED IN.
ACTUALLY, I WAS OUT SHOPPING FOR
GEAR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. THAT'S RIGHT.
I SHOULD UPDATE MY EQUIPMENT,
TOO.
I DON'T THINK THISIS GONNA BE
ENOUGH.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
I KNOW A GOOD WEAPON SHOP IN
TOWN.
BUT DO YOU HAVE ENOUGH MONEY?
'CAUSE THEY'RE NOT CHEAP.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, MONEY.
WAIT.
THIS THING CALLED "YULD" -- IS
THAT MONEY?
&gt;&gt; UH-HUH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, YUI?
WAKE UP. WE'RE HEADING OUT NOW.
&gt;&gt; [ Yawning ] OKAY.
&gt;&gt; HM?
[ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY'D WE COME HERE?
&gt;&gt; WELL, WHEN FLYING LONG
DISTANCES, IT'S BETTER IF YOU
START FROM A HIGHER ALTITUDE.
THAT'S WHAT THE TOWER'S HERE
FOR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME!!
[ ARMOR CLINKS ]
U-UH -- WAIT!
&gt;&gt; COME ON! LET'S GO!
I WANT TO GET PAST THE FOREST
BEFORE DARK.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; THIS WAY, SLOWPOKE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; LEAFA!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
OH. UH, HELLO, SIGURD.
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S THIS I HEAR ABOUT YOU
LEAVING THE PARTY?
IS THAT TRUE?
&gt;&gt; WELL...YEAH, IT IS.
&gt;&gt; DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW MUCH
THAT'S GOING TO UPSET THE OTHER
MEMBERS?
&gt;&gt; YOU SAID IT WOULDN'T BE A
PROBLEM IF I JOINED ONLY WHEN I
HAD THE TIME.
YOU ALSO SAID I COULD QUIT
WHENEVER I WANTED TO.
&gt;&gt; YES, I KNOW WHAT I SAID, BUT
YOU'VE BEEN WITH US FOR A WHILE
NOW.
EVERYONE KNOWS YOU.
IF YOU LEAVE US, IT'S GOING TO
DAMAGE THE REPUTATION OF THE
PARTY!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: PARTY MEMBERS ARE NOT
ITEMS.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT DID YOU SAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: PARTY MEMBERS AREN'T
ITEMS, SO DON'T EXPECT THEM TO
BE ON CALL FOR YOU.
THEY'RE NOT YOUR ARMOR.
THEY'RE NOT YOUR SWORD.
THEY'RE NOT YOUR EQUIPMENT.
&gt;&gt; YOU SON OF A...
I BET THAT BIG MOUTH OF YOURS
GOT YOU THROWN OUT OF YOUR OWN
TERRITORY.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT, YOU
PIECE OF SPRIGGAN TRASH.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, THAT'S IT! ENOUGH!
KIRITO'S MY NEW PARTNER, SO
LEAVE HIM ALONE!
&gt;&gt; WHAT?!
LEAFA!
YOU'RE ABANDONING US TO BE A
RENEGADE, LIKE HIM?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
YES.
I AM.
AND I'M NOT COMING BACK -- EVER!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN ABOUT YOU
BUZZING AROUND MY PARTY MEMBERS,
BUT IF YOU THINK YOU CAN STEAL
THEM, THEN THAT'S ANOTHER STORY.
IF YOU'RE STUPID ENOUGH TO WALTZ
INTO ANOTHER RACE'S TERRITORY,
THEN IT'S YOUR OWN DAMN FAULT IF
YOU GET KILLED, SPRIGGAN!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; THIS ISN'T THE TIME OR PLACE,
SIGURD.
IF WE GANK THIS GUY IN FRONT OF
ALL THESE PEOPLE, WE'RE GONNA
LOOK BAD.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
ONCE YOU CROSS OUR BORDER, YOU
BETTER RUN AND HIDE, LEAFA.
I NEVER EXPECTED YOU TO BETRAY
ME LIKE THIS.
NEVER.
BUT YOU'LL REGRET IT SOON
ENOUGH.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
I'M REALLY SORRY YOU GOT DRAGGED
INTO ALL THAT DRAMA.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S COOL.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU,THOUGH.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
&gt;&gt; UH...
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY! DON'T!
WOW.
THIS IS AN AMAZING VIEW.
THE SKY'S SO CLOSE, IT'S LIKE I
CAN REACH OUT AND TOUCH IT.
&gt;&gt; I KNOW, RIGHT?
WHENEVER I LOOK UP AT THAT SKY,
EVERYTHING ELSE FEELS SO SMALL.
THE TIMING COULDN'T HAVE BEEN
ANY BETTER.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT LEAVING
HERE FOR A WHILE NOW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, BUT...I FEEL
LIKE IT'S SORT OF MY FAULT YOU
LEFT ON BAD TERMS WITH THOSE
GUYS.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, WELL, I DON'T THINK IT
COULD HAVE HAPPENED ANY OTHER
WAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY
"RENEGADE"?
&gt;&gt; A RENEGADE'S A PLAYER WHO
ABANDONS THEIR TERRITORY.
IF YOU GET BRANDED AS ONE,
EVERYONE'S GONNA LOOK DOWN ON
YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AND YOU'RE COOL WITH
THAT?
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
I DON'T REALLY CARE.
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
EVERYONE'S SO QUICK TO TIE EACH
OTHER DOWN LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, WHAT'S THE POINT IN
HAVING WINGS, YOU KNOW?
&gt;&gt; YOU HUMANS ARE
SO COMPLICATED.
HONESTLY, YOUR PSYCHOLOGY IS
CONFUSING.
WHY DO YOU ACT SO HORRIBLY TO
EACH OTHER, WHEN ALL YOU WANT IS
COMPANIONSHIP?
&gt;&gt; WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
&gt;&gt; IF IT WERE ME...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
>> ...I'D DO THAT.
IT'S SIMPLE, STRAIGHTFORWARD,
AND EFFICIENT.
&gt;&gt; [ STAMMERS ]
THAT'S AN AMAZING A.I.
DO ALLPRIVATE PIXIES ACT LIKE
THAT, OR JUST YOURS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, JUST MINE, BUT
SHE'S A WEIRDO.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ BABBLING ]
&gt;&gt; I GUESS YOU WOULD KNOW, HUH?
"ALL WE WANT IS COMPANIONSHIP."
HUH.
&gt;&gt; LEAFA!
&gt;&gt; HEY, RECON.
&gt;&gt; HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?!
[ PANTING ]
YOU COULD HAVE AT LEAST SAID
SOMETHINGBEFORE YOU LEFT!
&gt;&gt; [ Laughing ] OH, SORRY.
I GUESS I FORGOT.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
WHY'D YOU QUIT THE PARTY ALL OF
A SUDDEN LIKE THAT?
&gt;&gt; WELL...I DIDN'T REALLY THINK
TOO HARD ABOUT IT.
I JUST DID IT.
WHAT ARE YOUGONNA DO, THOUGH?
&gt;&gt; AS IF, LEAFA!
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHERE YOU GO.
MY SWORD BELONGS TO YOU AND YOU
ALONE.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T NEED IT, BUT...
THANKS.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
W-W-WHAT I MEAN BY THAT WAS,
I'M GONNA GO WITH YOU --
WHEREVER.
THAT IS, I'D LIKETO GO, BUT
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT'S BEEN
BUGGING ME.
&gt;&gt; WHAT IS IT?
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T REALLY PROVE
ANYTHING YET, BUT THERE'S A FEW
THINGS I WANT TO LOOK INTO SOME
MORE, SO I'M GONNA STAY IN
SIGURD'S PARTY A LITTLE LONGER.
HEY, KIRITO?
SHE HAS A HABIT OF GETTING
HERSELF IN TROUBLE.
I'D APPRECIATE IT IF YOU KEEP AN
EYE ON HER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. SURE.
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
&gt;&gt; AND JUST TO MAKE SURE WE'RE
ABSOLUTELY CLEAR, LEAFA IS MY --
[ YELPS ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; WE'LL BE IN THE NEUTRAL ZONE
FOR A WHILE.
MESSAGE ME IF YOU NEED ANYTHING.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LET ME GET THIS
STRAIGHT.
IN REAL LIFE, HE'S YOUR FRIEND?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM-HMMMM.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, WHAT'S THAT WEIRD NOISE
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOTHING.
JUST A LITTLE JEALOUS, IS ALL.
>> NOW, THAT PERSON'S FEELINGS,
I CAN UNDERSTAND.
HE MUST LIKE YOU A LOT, WOULDN'T
YOU SAY, LEAFA?
DO YOU FEEL THE SAME WAY ABOUT
HIM?
&gt;&gt; [ SCOFFS ]
I-I DON'T KNOW!
GEEZ!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; [ Chuckling ] HURRY UP, YOU
GUYS!
LET'S TRY TO MAKE IT ALL THE WAY
TO THE LAKE WITHOUT STOPPING!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ INHALES SHARPLY ]
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
UNBELIEVABLE.
YOU CAN BE SO STUBBORN --
SERIOUSLY.
NO MATTER WHAT I DO, I CAN'T
HURT YOU.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT BODY'S REAL.
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST LOOSEN UP AND
ENJOY YOURSELF A LITTLE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I DON'T EXPECT YOU TO
UNDERSTAND, BUT TO ME, IT
DOESN'T MATTER IF MY BODY'S REAL
OR VIRTUAL.
YOU MAY NOT THINK THAT WAY, BUT
I DO.
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU AFRAID YOU'RE GOING
TO BE CORRUPTED SOMEHOW?
[ CHUCKLES ]
BECAUSE IF THAT'S THE CASE, YOU
DEFINITELY NEED TO TAKE THINGS A
LITTLE LESS SERIOUSLY WHILE
YOU'RE HERE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WELL, I'M NOT PLANNING
ON STAYING IN THIS CAGE FOREVER.
YOU'LL SEE.
HE'LL COME AND SAVE ME.
>> REALLY? WHO WILL?
THAT HERO BOYFRIEND OF YOURS?
GOES BY THE NAME OF KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
PLEASE.
YOU THINK I DIDN'T KNOW?
HIS REAL NAME'S KIRIGAYA.
I MET HIM THE OTHER DAY -- IN
THE REAL WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
I COULDN'T BELIEVE THAT WEAK
LITTLE BOY WAS THE SAME ONE WHO
BEAT SWORD ART ONLINE.
IT TOOK ME A SECOND TO COLLECT
MYSELF.
BY THE WAY, WHERE DO YOU THINK I
MET HIM?
IN YOUR HOSPITAL ROOM.
AS YOU WERE LYING THERE, I TOLD
HIM I'D BE MARRYING YOU NEXT
WEEK.
MY GOD, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN HIS
FACE.
IT WAS LIKE ALL THE COLOR
DRAINED OUT OF IT!
[ Laughing ] I COULD BARELY KEEP
MYSELF FROM LAUGHING!
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT I
THINK?
I'LL BET YOU ANYTHING THAT BRAT
WON'T HAVE THE GUTS TO PUT ON
THE NerveGear EVER AGAIN!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; THAT REMINDS ME -- I PROMISED
HIM I WAS GOING TO SEND ALONG A
WEDDING INVITATION.
I'M PRETTY SURE HE'LL COME.
HE'S GOING TO WANT TO SEE YOU IN
YOUR WEDDING DRESS.
I KNOW -- I'M GENEROUS.
THE LEAST I CAN DO IS LEAVE THE
LITTLE [Laughing] HERO A FEW
CRUMBS!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
WELL, I HAVE TO GET GOING NOW,
TITANIA.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MISS ME TOO
MUCH.
>> Asuna: HE'S ALIVE.
KIRITO'S ALIVE!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: 8...1, 1...
3, 2...3, 2...9.
&gt;&gt; [ SCREECHES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SHOUTS ]
&gt;&gt; SAY-AH SLEETA FIM-GLOWN
VEENDO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HM.
&gt;&gt; NICE JOB.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THANKS FOR THE
AWESOME BACKUP.
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
OUR WINGS AREN'T GONNA LAST MUCH
LONGER.
I THINK WE SHOULD LAND DOWN
THERE FOR A BIT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
[ BOTH GROANING ]
&gt;&gt; HEY, YOU GETTING TIRED YET?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOPE.
I'M GOOD TO GO.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, MR. TOUGH GUY.
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU, BUT
FLYING'S OUT FOR BOTH OF US FOR
A LITTLE WHILE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH? HOW COME?
&gt;&gt; YOU SEE THAT MOUNTAIN WAY
OVER THERE?
IT'S ABOVE THE ALTITUDE LIMIT,
SO WE CAN'T FLY OVER.
THE ONLY WAY ANYONE CAN PASS IT
IS TO GO THROUGH THE CAVES.
IT'S THE TOUGHEST PART OF THE
TRIP BETWEEN SYLPH TERRITORY AND
ARUM -- OR SO I'VE HEARD.
I'VE NEVER EVEN BEEN THIS FAR
MYSELF.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GUESS WE WALK.
THESE CAVES -- ARE THEY LONG?
&gt;&gt; PRETTY LONG.
THERE'S A MINING TOWN ABOUT
HALFWAY.
IT'S NEUTRAL TERRITORY, SO WE
CAN REST THERE.
THAT REMINDS ME -- ARE YOU GOOD
FOR TIME, OR DO YOU HAVE TO GET
BACK?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S 7:00 AT NIGHT IN
THE REAL WORLD.
YEAH, I CAN KEEP GOING FOR A
WHILE.
&gt;&gt; COOL.
I CAN, TOO, SO LET'S KEEP GOING.
BUT SINCE WE'RE HERE, WE SHOULD
ROTATE OUT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAIT -- ROTATE?
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
WE TAKE TURNS LOGGING OUT AND
RESTING WHILE THE OTHER KEEPS
WATCH.
YOU CAN'T LOG OUT WHEN YOU'RE IN
THE FIELD, REMEMBER?
SO WE HAVE TO TAKE TURNS LOGGING
OUT.
THE PERSON WHO STAYS BEHIND
GUARDS THE OTHER'S AVATAR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
LADIES FIRST.
&gt;&gt; OKAY. DON'T MIND IF I DO.
SEE YOU IN ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
[ WARBLE ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ SIGHS ]
WAAAH!
HEY, KAZUTO!
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO FOR
DINNER?
I WONDER IF HE'S ASLEEP.
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
[ GROANS ]
[ FAUCET SQUEAKS, WATER RUNS ]
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET BACK THERE.
[ MIRROR SQUEAKS ]
KIRITO.
IT'S NOT THAT I'M IN LOVE WITH
HIM OR ANYTHING, OR THAT I'VE
GOT SOMEONE TO GO ON ADVENTURES
WITH.
NO.
I'M JUST EXCITED I GET TO GO
PLACES IN A NEW WORLD.
&gt;&gt; HEY, I'M BACK!
DID YOU SEE ANY MONSTERS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Muffled ] NO, I
DIDN'T.
IT'S BEEN PRETTY QUIET THIS
WHOLE TIME.
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU EATING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I BOUGHT A BUNCH AT A
SHOP BEFORE WE LEFT SYLVAIN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
CALLED, BUT AN NPC SAID YOU CAN
ONLY GET THEM THERE.
&gt;&gt; I'VE NEVER SEEN THEM BEFORE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS, SCREAMS ]
[ COUGHING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Laughing ] SORRY TO
LEAVE YOU LIKE THIS, BUT IT IS
MY TURN.
KEEP ME SAFE, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; GET OUT OF HERE BEFORE I HURT
YOU!
[ COUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
NO WAY!
YOU CAN MOVE WHEN YOUR MASTER'S
LOGGED OUT?!
&gt;&gt; WELL, OF COURSE I CAN MOVE.
YOU KNOW, I'M MY OWN PERSON.
AND FOR YOUR INFORMATION, HE'S
NOT MY MASTER.
HE'S MY DADDY!
&gt;&gt; YEAH, ABOUT THAT --
I WAS GONNA ASK YOU BEFORE.
WHY DO YOU CALL HIM YOUR DADDY?
DID HE, YOU KNOW, UM, SET YOU
THAT WAY OR SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; HE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING TO MY
SETTINGS.
HE SAVED ME.
HE TOLD ME I WAS HIS DAUGHTER.
THAT MAKES HIM MY DADDY.
YOU SEE HOW THAT WORKS?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I...GUESS.
DO YOU, YOU KNOW...LIKE HIM?
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU MEAN
BY "LIKE."
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
IT MEANS YOU WANT TO BE WITH HIM
ALL THE TIME, AND WHEN YOU'RE
TOGETHER, YOU GET EXCITED ABOUT
BEING NEAR HIM...
OR...SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANS ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S WRONG, LEAFA?
&gt;&gt; NOTHING! IT'S NOTHING!
>> Kirito: WHAT'SNOTHING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT IS IT?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
&gt;&gt; WELCOME BACK, DADDY.
LEAFA WAS JUST EXPLAINING TO ME
WHAT IT MEANS WHEN SOMEONE SAYS
THEY LIKE S--
&gt;&gt; N-O-O-O!
I SAID IT'S NOTHING!
IT'S NOTHING!
[ Laughing nervously ] YOU
WEREN'T THERE FOR VERY LONG.
I HOPE YOU GOT SOMETHING TO EAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
MY FAMILY LEFT SOMETHING FOR ME,
SO I'M GOOD.
&gt;&gt; SWEET!
WELL, COME ON, THEN.
LET'S GET GOING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. LEAD THE WAY.
&gt;&gt; IS SOMETHING WRONG?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T KNOW.
IT SORT OF FELT LIKE SOMEONE WAS
WATCHING US.
HEY, YUI, THERE ANY PLAYERS
NEARBY?
&gt;&gt; NO, I'M NOT SENSING ANY OTHER
PLAYERS.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
IT'S POSSIBLE SOMEONE PUT A
TRACER ON US.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT THE HECK'S A
TRACER?
&gt;&gt; A KIND OF TRACKING MAGIC.
IT LOOKS LIKE A SMALL ANIMAL OR
AN INSECT.
IT TELLS THE CASTER A TARGET'S
POSITION.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CAN YOU DISPEL IT?
&gt;&gt; SURE -- IF YOU CAN FIND IT.
THE THING IS, IF THE CASTER'S
MAGIC SKILL IS HIGH, THE TRACER
CAN TRACK YOU FROM FAR AWAY.
IN A FIELD THIS SIZE, IT'D TAKE
FOREVER TO FIND IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GREAT.
EH, MAYBE IT'S JUST MY
IMAGINATION.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
&gt;&gt; [ CHITTERS ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]