[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ INDISTINCT TALKING, MUNCHING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
[ TALKING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE'S SO...
MANY OF 'EM, HUH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, THERE ARE.
&gt;&gt; I KNOW, RIGHT?
IT'S LIKE THIS PRETTY MUCH EVERY
DAY.
BY THE WAY, IS YUI FEELING ANY
BETTER?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, SHE GOT A GOOD
NIGHT'S SLEEP, SO I THINK SHE'S
OKAY.
&gt;&gt; MMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T KNOW.
YOU TELL ME.
&gt;&gt; HAS THIS EVER HAPPENED TO HER
BEFORE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU SEE, WE FOUND HER ON FLOOR
22, WANDERING IN THE FOREST.
THE POOR THING -- SHE'S LOST HER
MEMORY.
&gt;&gt; OH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THAT'S THE REASON WE
CAME HERE.
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE THOUGHT MAYBE
SOMEONE IN THE
TOWN OF BEGINNINGS MIGHT KNOW
WHO SHE IS.
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU LIVE HERE.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN HER BEFORE?
&gt;&gt; UH...
SORRY, I HAVEN'T.
I MEAN, THERE ARE A LOT OF KIDS
IN TOWN, BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN
HER.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
WHEN THE GAME STARTED, A LOT OF
THE CHILDREN SUFFERED SEVERE
PSYCHOLOGICAL TRAUMA.
I COULDN'T STAND BY AND DO
NOTHING, SO I MOVED TO THIS
CHURCH AND MADE IT A SAFE PLACE
FOR THEM TO LIVE.
I WALKED THROUGH THE TOWN EVERY
DAY, LOOKING FOR KIDS LIKE
THESE, KIDS WHO MIGHT NEED MY
HELP, BUT IN ALL THIS TIME, I'VE
NEVER SEEN HER BEFORE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BACK TO SQUARE ONE.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
I'M YULIER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AND YOU'RE WITH THE
ARMY, RIGHT?
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT HERE TO START
TROUBLE BECAUSE OF YESTERDAY.
&gt;&gt; GOD, NO.
IN FACT, I'M HERE TO THANK YOU.
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; YOU DID RIGHT BY PUTTING
THOSE MEN IN THEIR PLACE.
&gt;&gt; Both: HUH?
&gt;&gt; ACTUALLY, I CAME HERE TO ASK
THE TWO OF YOU FOR YOUR HELP.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SERIOUSLY?
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ WOMAN CONTINUES SINGING ]
&gt;&gt; WHEN THE GUILD WAS FORMED,
WE -- WELL, ACTUALLY, IT WAS OUR
LEADER, THINKER.
HE NEVER WANTED IT TO TURN INTO
THE KIND OF DICTATORIAL
ORGANIZATION IT'S BECOME.
AT FIRST, THE MISSION OF THE
GUILD WAS TO SHARE INFORMATION
AND FOOD EQUALLY AMONG AS MANY
PLAYERS AS POSSIBLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT THEN THE GUILD
GREW TOO LARGE, DIDN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; RIGHT.
AND AFTER MUCH INFIGHTING, ONE
MAN BECAME VERY POWERFUL.
HIS NAME IS KIBAOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; KIBAOU AND HIS GROUP BECAME
STRONGER AND STRONGER,
MONOPOLIZING ALL THE BEST
MONSTER SPAWN POINTS.
THEY'RE OUT OF CONTROL NOW,
EXTORTING OTHER PLAYERS UNDER
THE PRETEXT OF COLLECTING TAXES.
IT WAS OBVIOUS KIBAOU DIDN'T
CARE ABOUT CLEARING THE GAME,
AND THAT MADE A LOT OF PEOPLE
MAD.
HE HAD TO DO SOMETHING TO GET
BACK IN THEIR GOOD GRACES, SO HE
SENT THE HIGHEST-LEVEL PLAYERS
HE HAD TO THE FRONT LINES.
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: CORVATZ!
&gt;&gt; KIBAOU WAS DENOUNCED AFTER
SPEARHEADING THAT MASSACRE.
THAT'S WHEN WE STARTED TO
SERIOUSLY CONSIDER KICKING HIM
OUT OF THE GUILD FOR GOOD.
AND NOW THAT HE'S SCARED AND
GETTING DESPERATE, HE'S DECIDED
TO ELIMINATE THINKER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; HE SET A TRAP AND STRANDED
THINKER DEEP INSIDE A DUNGEON.
[ ALL GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CAN'T HE TELEPORT
OUT?
&gt;&gt; MNH-MNH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: DOES HE HAVE ANY
WEAPONS?
&gt;&gt; HE DIDN'T TAKE ANYTHING WITH
HIM.
KIBAOU TOLD HIM HE WANTED TO
TALK, UNARMED.
THINKER BELIEVED HIM.
THAT WAS THREE DAYS AGO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HE'S BEEN GONE THAT
LONG?
CAN'T HE FIND HIS WAY OUT?
&gt;&gt; THE DUNGEON IS THE HIGHEST
LEVEL WE'VE SEEN SO FAR.
HE CAN'T GET OUT OF THERE ON HIS
OWN.
AS HIS SECOND-IN-COMMAND, THIS
IS MY RESPONSIBILITY.
BUT THE PROBLEM IS, MY LEVEL
ISN'T HIGH ENOUGH TO REACH HIM.
AND KIBAOU IS USING HIS
INFLUENCE TO KEEP THE REST OF
THE ARMY FROM HELPING ME.
WHEN I HEARD THAT TWO OF THE
MOST POWERFUL PLAYERS ANYONE'S
SEEN WERE IN TOWN, I THOUGHT,
"THIS IS MY CHANCE."
I TRACKED YOU DOWN BECAUSE I
NEED YOUR HELP.
KIRITO, ASUNA, I BEG YOU FOR
THINKER'S SAKE, PLEASEHELP ME
RESCUE HIM FROM THAT DUNGEON!
[ BOTH SIGH ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF YOU THINK WE CAN
HELP GET THINKER OUT OF THERE,
WE'D BE GLAD TO HELP YOU.
HOWEVER...
WELL, THE THING IS, WE'D LIKE TO
MAKE SURE YOU'RE TELLING THE
TRUTH.
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY.
I KNOW WE JUST MET, AND I'M
ASKING A LOT FROM YOU.
BUT WHEN I THINK ABOUT HIM
TRAPPED ALONE IN THERE, I FEEL
LIKE I'M GOING INSANE!
&gt;&gt; IT'S OKAY, MOMMY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH?
&gt;&gt; EVERYTHING SHE'S BEEN TELLING
YOU IS THE TRUTH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: Y-YUI, YOU MEAN YOU
CAN TELL?
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I KNOW SHE IS,
BUT...
SHE IS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ LAUGHS ]
IF ANYTHING, I'D RATHER TRUST
HER AND REGRET IT THAN NOT TRUST
HER AND REGRET IT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LET'S GO.
IT'LL ALL WORK OUT.
RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES ]
WHATEVER YOU SAY, MR. EASYGOING.
OKAY, WE'LL HELP.
I JUST HOPE WE'RE STRONG ENOUGH
TO DO IT.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU SO MUCH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I KNOW WHAT IT FEELS
LIKE TO WANT TO SAVE SOMEONE,
ESPECIALLY SOMEONE YOU CARE FOR.
&gt;&gt; [ SNIFFLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: STAY HERE AND WAIT
FOR US, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; NO, I'M COMING, TOO!
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON, YUI.
DON'T YOU WANT TO STAY HERE WITH
&gt;&gt; NO!
&gt;&gt; UH...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GREAT, NOW WE GET TO
SEE HER REBELLIOUS SIDE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HEY, THIS IS SERIOUS.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS FOR YOU TO
COME ALONG WITH US THIS TIME.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
I'M GOING, TOO!
[ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I NEVER KNEW THIS
DUNGEON WAS UNDER THE
TOWN OF BEGINNINGS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW.
THERE WASN'T ANYTHING LIKE THIS
DURING THE BETA TEST.
&gt;&gt; I THINK THE DUNGEON OPENS UP
TO REVEAL MORE AS THE FLOORS
ABOVE ARE CLEARED.
I BET KIBAOU WAS PLANNING ON
KEEPING THIS PLACE ALL TO
HIMSELF.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EXCLUSIVE ACCESS TO
SPAWNS CAN BE PROFITABLE.
&gt;&gt; THE THING IS, THE MONSTERS
HERE ARE USUALLY AROUND LEVEL
HE WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO DO MUCH
HUNTING.
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
THIS IS THE ENTRANCE.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
DON'T WORRY -- I'M NOT AFRAID!
&gt;&gt; UH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO, IT'S OKAY.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, SHE'S A HECK
OF A LOT TOUGHER THAN SHE LOOKS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM-HMM.
SHE'LL MAKE A FINE SWORDSWOMAN
SOMEDAY.
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM!
[ LAUGHTER ]
&gt;&gt; WE SHOULD GET GOING.
[ FOOTSTEPS PATTERING ]
[ CREATURES WARBLING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SHOUTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME HERE, LITTLE
FROGGY!
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD
APOLOGIZE.
HE'S DOING ALL THE FIGHTING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, NO.
HE'S HAPPY OUT THERE.
REALLY, HE LOVES GETTING HIS
BATTLE ON.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE'RE PRETTY FAR DOWN.
ARE WE ALMOST THERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING
CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; THINKER HASN'T MOVED FROM
THIS POSITION FOR A WHILE NOW.
&gt;&gt; OH, OH!
&gt;&gt; IT COULD BE A SAFE ZONE, BUT
I'M NOT SURE.
IF WE CAN REACH IT, MAYBE WE CAN
USE A TELEPORT CRYSTAL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHEW!
MAN, I FOUGHT MY BUTT OFF!
&gt;&gt; I SHOULD'VE HELPED YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, NOT AT ALL.
I HAD A BLAST.
BESIDES, THEY DROPPED SOME
ITEMS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: REALLY?
YOU GET ANYTHING GOOD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
WHAT -- WHAT IS THAT?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S SCAVENGED TOAD
MEAT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU MEAN THOSE FROGS?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, THE WEIRDER THE
MEAT, THE BETTER THE TASTE.
MAYBE YOU CAN COOK IT UP LATER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NOT ON YOUR LIFE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT THE HELL?!
OH, COME ON, WHAT'D YOU DO THAT
FOR?!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMPH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DAMN IT! OKAY, FINE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMM?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT AM I GONNA DO
WITH THESE?!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
NO! NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA!
IT'S GOOD MEAT!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: GET RID OF IT!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT IT'S DELICIOUS!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: EW!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU JUST HAVE TO COOK
IT RIGHT!
&gt;&gt; YOU SMILED.
&gt;&gt; UH?
&gt;&gt; Both: HUH?
&gt;&gt; I'VE NEVER EVER SEEN YOU
SMILE BEFORE!
&gt;&gt; UH?
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
COME ON, LET'S GO.
LOOK, IT'S A SAFE ZONE.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE'S A PLAYER
INSIDE.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
IT'S THINKER!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAIT, DON'T!
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; YULIER!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ] THINKER!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; NO, STAY AWAY!
THE CORRIDOR'S RIGGED!
[ ALARM BLARES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
STOP! WAIT, YULIER!
COME BACK!
&gt;&gt; UNH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YULIER.
&gt;&gt; UH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: TAKE HER TO THE SAFE
ZONE AND WAIT FOR US THERE,
OKAY?
&gt;&gt; O-OKAY.
&gt;&gt; MOMMY...
&gt;&gt; COME ON.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA, USE A TELEPORT
CRYSTAL AND GET YUI AND THE
OTHERS OUT OF HERE NOW.
I CAN'T SEE ITS DATA WITH MY
I.D. SKILL.
IT COULD BE AS STRONG AS
SOMETHING FROM FLOOR 90.
I CAN BUY YOU TIME.
JUST GET EVERYONE OUT OF HERE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO WAY AM I LEAVING
YOU HERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL CATCH UP!
MOVE IT!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; MOMMY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
TAKE CARE OF YUI!
RUN WHILE YOU STILL HAVE A
CHANCE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA!
&gt;&gt; NO, WE CAN'T LEAVE --
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HURRY!
&gt;&gt; UH?
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BOTH SHOUT ]
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
[ CREATURE GROWLS ]
[ GROANING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ] KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; YUI, NO!
&gt;&gt; IT'S DANGEROUS!
COME BACK!
[ CREATURE GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ CREATURE GROWLS ]
[ GRUNTS ] WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
GET AWAY FROM IT!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YUI!
[ CREATURE GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; DADDY, MOMMY, IT'S OKAY.
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YUI!
[ GROWLING CONTINUES ]
[ GASPS ]
AN IMMORTAL OBJECT?!
[ CREATURE GROWLS ]
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ WHISTLING CONTINUES ]
[ CREATURE GROWLING ]
[ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPING ]
[ CREATURE SHRIEKING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GROANING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH, YUI?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI...
&gt;&gt; DADDY, MOMMY...
DON'T WORRY -- I REMEMBER
EVERYTHING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YUI, SAY SOMETHING.
YOU REMEMBER WHO YOU ARE?
&gt;&gt; YES.
KIRITO, ASUNA.
[ BOTH GASP ]
EVERYTHING IN THE WORLD OF
SWORD ART ONLINE IS CONTROLLED
BY A SINGLE MASSIVE SYSTEM.
THE SYSTEM IS CALLED CARDINAL.
IT WAS DESIGNED TO OPERATE
ENTIRELY ON ITS OWN WITHOUT ANY
HUMAN INTERVENTION.
ITS FUNCTION IS TO REGULATE THE
BALANCE OF S.A.O. ACCORDING TO
ITS OWN DISCRETION.
FROM MONSTERS AND NPC A.I. TO
DROP RATES FOR ITEMS AND MONEY,
EVERYTHING HERE IS CONTROLLED BY
THE PROCESSES THE CARDINAL
PROGRAM EXECUTES.
THAT INCLUDES THE PSYCHOLOGICAL
CARE OF THE PLAYERS.
MENTAL HEALTH COUNSELING
PROGRAM, PROTOTYPE ONE.
CODE NAME -- YUI.
THAT IS WHO I AM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
YOU'RE A PROGRAM?
AN A.I.?
&gt;&gt; I WAS DESIGNED TO PUT PLAYERS
AT EASE WITH ME.
THAT'S WHY I WAS GIVEN THE
ABILITY TO EMULATE COMPLEX
EMOTIONS.
NOTHING ABOUT ME IS REAL,
NOTHING, NOT EVEN MY TEARS.
I'M SO SORRY, ASUNA.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, YUI...
UH? [ SIGHS ]
BUT THEN WHAT ABOUT YOUR
AMNESIA?
CAN THAT EVEN HAPPEN TO AN A.I.?
&gt;&gt; TWO YEARS AGO, ON THE DAY OF
THE OFFICIAL LAUNCH AND FOR
REASONS I NEVER UNDERSTOOD, THE
CARDINAL PROGRAM BANNED ME FROM
INTERACTING WITH ANY OF THE
PLAYERS.
I WASN'T ALLOWED TO ASSIST THEM.
I COULDN'T DO ANYTHING EXCEPT
CONTINUE MONITORING THEIR MENTAL
STATES.
THEIR SITUATION, IN A WORD, WAS
HORRIBLE.
[ GASPS ] NO, DON'T!
[ GASPS ]
TERROR, DESPAIR, RAGE.
PEOPLE WERE OVERCOME BY NEGATIVE
FEELINGS.
SOME OF THEM COULDN'T TAKE IT.
THEY WENT INSANE.
UNDER NORMAL CIRCUMSTANCES, MY
FUNCTION WOULD HAVE BEEN TO GO
TO SUCH PLAYERS IMMEDIATELY.
BUT I WASN'T PERMITTED ANY
CONTACT WITH THEM.
LITTLE BY LITTLE, ERRORS BEGAN
PILING UP INSIDE OF ME.
AND I FELL APART.
THEN ONE DAY, I SAW TWO PLAYERS.
THEIR MENTAL PARAMETERS WERE
VASTLY DIFFERENT FROM ANYTHING
I'D SEEN AMONG THE OTHERS.
THERE WAS JOY.
AND PEACE.
AND THERE WAS SOMETHING MORE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; I WANDERED THROUGH THE
PLAYING FIELD, HOPING TO GET AS
CLOSE TO BOTH OF YOU AS I COULD
WITHOUT BEING DETECTED.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO THAT'S WHY YOU WERE
IN THE FOREST.
&gt;&gt; YES, THAT'S WHY.
I'VE WANTED TO MEET THE TWO OF
YOU FOR THE LONGEST TIME.
THAT'S STRANGE, ISN'T IT?
IT SHOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE FOR ME
TO THINK THINGS LIKE THAT.
[ SNIFFLES ]
I'M NOT HUMAN.
I'M A PROGRAM, AFTER ALL.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
YUI...
MAYBE WHAT YOU'RE FEELING ARE
REAL HUMAN EMOTIONS.
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERS ]
I DON'T KNOW. I'M CONFUSED.
NOTHING MAKES SENSE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENED TO
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU AREN'T JUST SOME
PROGRAM ANYMORE.
THE SYSTEM CAN'T CONTROL YOU.
LISTEN, IF YOU WANT SOMETHING,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SAY IT.
GO AHEAD, TELL US WHAT YOU WANT.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
MM. WHAT I WANT...
I WANT...
I WANT TO STAY WITH YOU FOREVER!
[ SIGHS ] DADDY!
MOMMY! [ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CRYING ]
YOU WILL!
WE'LL BE TOGETHER FOREVER, YUI.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
REMEMBER, YOU'RE OUR CHILD.
&gt;&gt; IT'S TOO LATE.
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: FOR WHAT?
&gt;&gt; LOOK, THIS IS ACTUALLY A
CONSOLE THE G.M. CAN USE TO GAIN
EMERGENCY ACCESS TO THE SYSTEM.
I USED IT TO DELETE THE MONSTER
IN THE CORRIDOR.
AND NOW BECAUSE I DISOBEYED THE
CARDINAL'S DIRECTIVE, THE SYSTEM
IS RUNNING A CHECK ON MY
PROGRAM.
IT THINKS I'M A FOREIGN OBJECT
NOW.
I'LL PROBABLY BE DELETED AT
ONCE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
OH, NO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE'S GOT TO BE A
WAY AROUND IT!
&gt;&gt; DADDY, MOMMY, THANK YOU.
THIS IS GOODBYE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
[ CRYING ]
NO! I DON'T WANT THAT!
STAY WITH US!
PLEASE STAY!
WE JUST STARTED LIVING LIKE A
REAL FAMILY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI, DON'T GO!
&gt;&gt; WHENEVER THE TWO OF YOU ARE
AROUND, YOU HAVE A WAY OF MAKING
PEOPLE SMILE.
FROM NOW ON AND FOR ME, PLEASE
CONTINUE MY WORK.
KEEP HELPING PEOPLE.
SHARE YOUR HAPPINESS WITH ALL OF
THEM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I CAN'T! I WON'T!
YOU HAVE TO STAY WITH US!
I CAN'T BE HAPPY WITHOUT YOU!
[ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; SMILE, MOMMY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CRYING CONTINUES ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GASPING ]
[ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
CARDINAL!
NO! KAYABA!
[ GRUNTS ]
YOU'RE GONNA FIND OUT THINGS
DON'T ALWAYS GO THE WAY YOU WANT
'EM TO!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
KIRITO, WHAT ARE YOU --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF I'M FAST ENOUGH, I
MIGHT BE ABLE TO USE THE G.M.'s
ACCOUNT TO ACCESS THE SYSTEM.
[ MONITOR WHIRRING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ WHIRRING CONTINUES ]
AGH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO!
[ SIGHS ] ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S THIS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THE SYSTEM WAS ABOUT
TO REJECT YUI'S ADMIN
CREDENTIALS.
THE ONLY THING I COULD DO WAS
TAKE HER PROGRAM AND TURN IT
INTO A GAME OBJECT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO THIS IS...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE HOLDING YUI'S
HEART.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; BYE!
&gt;&gt; BYE-BYE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HEY, KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF THE GAME DOES GET
CLEARED AND THIS WORLD ENDS,
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO YUI?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T WORRY -- I
FIXED IT, SO HER DATA WILL BE
SAVED TO THE LOCAL MEMORY ON MY
NerveGear.
WHEN WE GET BACK, RE-CREATING
HER THE WAY SHE WAS ISN'T GONNA
BE EASY.
BUT IF THERE'S A WAY, WE'LL FIND
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY.
AS LONG AS WE CAN BE A FAMILY
AGAIN.
WE'LL SEE HER WHEN WE GET
BACK -- OUR FIRST CHILD.
[ WHISTLING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, WE'LL SEE HER
AGAIN.
HEY, ASUNA, YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; GOOD LUCK, MOMMY.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ WOMAN CONTINUES SINGING ]