[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU CATCH ANYTHING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN TO SNEAK UP
ON YOU LIKE THAT.
MY NAME'S NISHIDA, AND I'M A
FISHERMAN -- IN THE GAME,
ANYWAY.
BACK IN JAPAN, I WAS THE HEAD OF
NETWORK SECURITY FOR A COMPANY
CALLED TOTO HIGH-SPEED INTERNET.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M KIRITO.
WAIT.
WASN'T TOTO THE COMPANY THAT --
&gt;&gt; YUP.
WE WERE THE FOLKS IN CHARGE OF
NETWORK SECURITY FOR THIS GAME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ ROD CREAKS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S A BIG ONE!
&gt;&gt; YEAH!
BUT I'VE CAUGHT BIGGER!
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA!
AWESOME!
&gt;&gt; THANKS.
I'M GOOD AT CATCHING 'EM, BUT
COOKING 'EM?
YEAH, NOT SO GOOD.
I'D LOVE TO MAKE SASHIMI OR A
NICE STEW OUT OF 'EM.
BUT WHAT'S THE POINT WHEN I
DON'T HAVE ANY SOY SAUCE?
I COULD GO FOR FISH BAKED WITH
SOY SAUCE RIGHT NOW OR WITH
RADISHES AND SOY SAUCE, YEAH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, UH, IF YOU WANT,
I JUST MIGHT BE ABLE TO HELP YOU
OUT WITH THAT.
&gt;&gt; WAIT! SAY WHAAAAAAAAAT?!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
AHH!
THAT WAS AN AMAZING MEAL.
I HAD NO IDEA YOU COULD GET SOY
SAUCE IN THIS WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: ACTUALLY, I MADE IT
MYSELF.
IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN TAKE SOME
HOME WITH YOU.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
MA'AM, MY TASTE BUDS BOW DOWN
BEFORE YOU!
[ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: GLAD YOU LIKED IT.
BY THE WAY, HOW HIGH IS YOUR
FISHING SKILL?
I'M ASKING BECAUSE KIRITO HASN'T
BEEN ABLE TO CATCH ANYTHING YET.
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, WELL, MAYBE IF
ALL THE LAKES ON THIS FLOOR
WEREN'T SO HARD.
&gt;&gt; WELL, ACTUALLY, THAT'S NOT
TRUE.
AS FAR AS FISHING GOES, THE ONLY
LAKE THAT'S TOUGH TO CATCH
ANYTHING IN IS THE BIG ONE YOU
WERE AT TODAY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT?!
WHY WOULD SOMEONE DESIGN IT LIKE
THAT?
&gt;&gt; YES! GOOD QUESTION!
THAT LAKE IS THE HOME OF...
THE KING OF ALL FISH.
&gt;&gt; Both: SERIOUSLY?
&gt;&gt; YUP. WE'RE OLD PALS.
I'VE HAD HIM ON THE END OF MY
HOOK QUITE A FEW TIMES.
BUT HE'S SO STRONG, HE YANKS THE
POLE RIGHT OUT OF MY HANDS EVERY
TIME.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; I WAS WONDERING...
DO YOU HAVE ANY PLANS FOR
TOMORROW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
I DON'T MIND HELPING THE OLD GUY
OUT, BUT HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
A SWITCH MOVE WITH A FISHING
POLE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE I
KNOW WHO CAN FIGURE IT OUT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT IF YOU CATCH IT?
WILL YOU KEEP IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IS THAT EVEN
POSSIBLE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HE IS PRETTY COOL,
THOUGH, DON'T YOU THINK?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GIGGLES ]
WHEN YOU BOTH SHOWED UP, I WAS
LIKE, "WHO IS THIS PERSON?"
ISN'T IT FUNNY HOW PEOPLE ARE
LIVING NORMAL LIVES IN THIS
WORLD?
AND SINCE WE'RE THE ONES ON THE
FRONT LINES, THEIR LIVES HAVE
SORT OF BECOME OUR
RESPONSIBILITY, HAVEN'T THEY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: FOR ME, I WASN'T
GETTING STRONGER FOR ANYONE
ELSE.
IT WAS JUST ABOUT ME STAYING
ALIVE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: EVERYONE EXPECTS GREAT
THINGS FROM YOU NOW.
AND GUESS WHAT. SO DO I.
TALK ABOUT PRESSURE, HUH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
I PROMISED I'D SAVE EVERYONE.
HELL OF A THING TO LIVE UP TO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, WELL.
THEY'LL UNDERSTAND IF YOU TAKE
TONIGHT OFF.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
OH, MY GOD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: CAN YOU BELIEVE ALL
THE PEOPLE WHO SHOWED UP?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; WELL, HERE WE GO!
THANKS FOR YOUR PATIENCE,
EVERYONE.
HERE COMES TODAY'S MAIN EVENT!
&gt;&gt; IT'S ABOUT TIME!
&gt;&gt; KIRITO, LET'S CATCH US A
FISH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. HMM?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HOW BIG'S THIS THING
SUPPOSED TO BE, ANYWAY?
&gt;&gt; OKAY, HERE GOES NOTHIN'!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SPECTATORS GASP ]
[ SPECTATORS WHISPERING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UM, SHOULDN'T YOU
REEL IT IN?
&gt;&gt; NO, NOT YET.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, NISHIDA?
&gt;&gt; HANG ON. NOT YET.
NOW! I GOT THE SUCKER!
[ GRUNTING ]
HERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, SWITCH?
[ GRUNTS ]
COME HERE, YOU BASTARD!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LOOK! IT'S COMING UP!
[ SPECTATORS MURMUR ]
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I THINK I TIRED HIM
OUT.
W-WHERE YOU GOIN'?! HEY!
AAH!
NO! NO! NO! NO!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO!
LOOK OUT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: FOR WHAT?
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAAAH!
YOU RAN AWAY!
YOU LEFT ME THERE TO DIE!
[ FISH GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; HERE IT COMES!
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA. IT CAN RUN?
IT'S LIKE A CRAZY LUNGFISH.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO! THIS IS SERIOUS!
THAT THING'S COMIN' FOR US!
HURRY! DO SOMETHING!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I'M STILL
THINKING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
GUESS I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
&gt;&gt; RUN WHILE YOU STILL CAN!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NAH, SHE'LL BE FINE.
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; SAVE YOUR WIFE, KIRITO!
[ YELPS ]
NO! WATCH OUT!
[ SPECTATORS GASP ]
&gt;&gt; WOW.
THAT WAS BADASS!
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE ASUNA, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
&gt;&gt; MAN, THIS IS AWESOME!
&gt;&gt; I'M A BIG FAN OF YOURS!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; CAN I SHAKE YOUR HAND?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NICE JOB, HONEY.
[ BEEPING ]
HEATHCLIFF?
[ DOOR OPENS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: COME ON, YOU'VE MOPED
LONG ENOUGH ALREADY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW.
BUT IT'S ONLY BEEN TWO WEEKS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF HE NEEDS US ON THE
FRONT LINES, THEN SOMETHING
MUST'VE HAPPENED.
WHY ELSE WOULD HE INTERRUPT OUR
VACATION?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, BUT STILL...
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LET'S AT LEAST HEAR
WHAT HE'S GOT TO SAY.
COME ON. TIME TO GO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE'LL TAKE CARE OF
THIS, THEN COME BACK.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU GOT IT.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
THANKS FOR SEEING US OFF.
I KNOW WE DIDN'T GET TO SPEND
MUCH TIME TOGETHER, BUT IT WAS
FUN.
&gt;&gt; OH, WELL, IT WAS AN HONOR AND
A PRIVILEGE.
ACTUALLY, BEFORE I MET THE TWO
OF YOU, I COULDN'T IMAGINE WHAT
THE FOLKS WORKING TO CLEAR THE
GAME WERE LIKE.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL HAVE BEEN FROM
ANOTHER PLANET.
BEING TRAPPED IN HERE FOR THE
PAST TWO YEARS...
[ SIGHS ]
...EVEN IF I MADE IT OUT ALIVE,
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN GO BACK TO
MY OLD JOB, MY OLD LIFE.
MAYBE DEEP DOWN INSIDE, I'VE
GIVEN UP HOPE OF EVER GETTIN'
OUT.
I FIGURED SPENDING MY TIME WITH
A FISHING POLE BETWEEN MY MITTS
WAS THE BEST THING FOR ME.
PRETTY SAD, HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UNH-UNH.
THAT ISN'T SAD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I GET WHAT YOU MEAN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I USED TO FEEL THE
SAME AS YOU -- AT FIRST, ANYWAY.
I FELT LOST AND HOPELESS.
EVERY NIGHT, I'D CRY MYSELF TO
SLEEP.
IT FELT LIKE EACH DAY THAT WENT
BY IN HERE WAS ANOTHER DAY LOST
FROM MY REAL LIFE.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO I'D CRY, AND
AFTERWARDS, I'D GO AND FIGHT AS
HARD AS I COULD.
ALL I CARED ABOUT WAS WINNING,
GETTING STRONGER, AND GETTING TO
THE NEXT FLOOR.
BUT THEN, I WAS WALKING ALONG
AND I SAW SOMEONE TAKING A NAP
IN THE SHADE.
I WAS SO MAD.
I TOLD HIM HE SHOULDN'T WASTE
HIS TIME LIKE THAT.
AND THEN HE SAID -- AND I'LL
NEVER FORGET IT -- "THIS IS
AINCRAD'S BEST SEASON, AND
TODAY'S WEATHER IS AT ITS
OPTIMAL SETTING!"
HE SAID IT'D BE A WASTE TO GO
INTO SOME DUNGEON ON SUCH A
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
SO I TRIED LYING DOWN, TOO, AND
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I SLEPT LIKE A BABY.
WHEN I WOKE UP, IT WAS EVENING
AND HE WAS GIVING ME THE
WEIRDEST LOOK.
ANYWAY, WE FORMED OUR OWN PARTY.
AND THAT'S WHEN I REALIZED
SOMETHING.
EVEN IN A WORLD LIKE THIS, HE
WAS REALLY LIVING.
HE WASN'T LOSING A DAY IN THE
REAL WORLD.
HE WAS GAINING A DAY HERE.
I LEARNED SO MUCH FROM HIM.
AND BY "HIM," I MEAN KIRITO.
WHEN I THOUGHT ABOUT HIM BEFORE
FALLING ASLEEP, I NOTICED I
WOULDN'T HAVE NIGHTMARES.
I BEGAN LOOKING FORWARD TO
SEEING HIM AGAIN.
IT WAS LIKE, FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I WAS GLAD I WAS HERE.
KIRITO IS EVERYTHING TO ME.
HE'S WHAT THE LAST TWO YEARS
WERE ABOUT.
HE'S PROOF I'M ALIVE.
WHY'D I PUT ON THE NerveGear
THAT DAY?
IT'S OBVIOUS.
SO I COULD COME HERE AND MEET
HIM.
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE, RIGHT?
YOU MUST HAVE SOMETHING TO LIVE
FOR, TOO.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH, YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
LIFE ISN'T SO BAD HERE.
NO, IT'S ACTUALLY PRETTY DAMN
GOOD.
I WISH THERE WAS SOMETHING I
COULD DO TO HELP, BUT WELL,
THERE IT IS.
GOOD LUCK AND BE SAFE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL GO FISHING AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: TAKE CARE, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Both: TELEPORT -- GRANDZAM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THE RECON TEAM WAS
WIPED OUT?
&gt;&gt; THEY WERE SCOUTING FOR THE
UPCOMING BOSS FIGHT.
IT WAS A PARTY OF 20 MEMBERS,
TAKEN FROM FIVE DIFFERENT
GUILDS.
10 OF THEM REACHED THE CENTER OF
THE ROOM...
THEN THE BOSS APPEARED.
AND THAT'S WHEN THE ENTRANCE
CLOSED, CUTTING THEM OFF FROM
THE REST OF THE PARTY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEY WALKED INTO AN
ANTI-CRYSTAL ZONE.
&gt;&gt; PRECISELY.
AND IT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN MORE
THAN FIVE MINUTES OR SO WHEN THE
DOOR FINALLY OPENED.
THE ROOM WAS EMPTY.
THERE WASN'T ANY TRACE LEFT
BEHIND OF THE 10 SOLDIERS OR THE
BOSS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE KIDDING!
&gt;&gt; NOW MORE THAN EVER, CLEARING
THE GAME SHOULD BE EVERYONE'S
NUMBER-ONE PRIORITY.
WE'RE GOING TO LAUNCH AN ATTACK
WITH THE LARGEST GROUP WE CAN
ASSEMBLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU CAN COUNT ON US
TO FIGHT WITH YOU.
BUT THIS NEEDS TO BE CLEAR.
ASUNA'S SAFETY IS MY PRIORITY.
IF THINGS START TO GET HAIRY IN
THERE, I'M GONNA PROTECT HER.
THAT'S NOT NEGOTIABLE.
&gt;&gt; A PERSON WITH SOMETHING TO
PROTECT IS A STRONG ALLY TO
HAVE.
I'M EXPECTING A GOOD FIGHT FROM
YOU.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THREE MORE HOURS OF
WAITING.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE'S SOMETHING I
HAVE TO ASK YOU.
BUT I DON'T WANT YOU GETTING MAD
AT ME.
INSTEAD OF GOING TO THE BOSS
FIGHT, COULD YOU PLEASE STAY
HERE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHY WOULD YOU ASK
THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE WON'T BE ABLE TO
USE TELEPORT CRYSTALS, SO
THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT COULD
HAPPEN.
I'M SCARED.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENED TO YOU,
I --
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO YOU WANT TO GO TO
SOMEPLACE DANGEROUS...ALONE.
AND YOU EXPECT ME TO STAY HERE,
WHERE IT'S SAFE?
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF
YOU DIDN'T COME BACK, HUH?
I'D KILL MYSELF!
I'D NEVER FORGIVE MYSELF FOR
STAYING BEHIND, SO WHAT WOULD BE
THE POINT IN LIVING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M SORRY!
I GUESS I'M LOSING MY NERVE.
ALL I WANT TO DO IS RUN AWAY
WITH YOU.
I DON'T CARE IF WE NEVER MAKE IT
BACK TO THE REAL WORLD.
I JUST WANT TO LIVE WITH YOU IN
OUR LITTLE HOUSE IN THE WOODS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IT'D BE NICE IF WE
COULD DO THAT -- BE TOGETHER
EVERY DAY FOREVER.
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN THE REAL
WORLD?
ABOUT WHAT'S HAPPENING TO OUR
BODIES WHILE WE'RE IN HERE?
A FEW WEEKS AFTER THE GAME WAS
LAUNCHED, DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT
HAPPENED?
MOST OF THE PLAYERS SUDDENLY
WENT OFFLINE AND STAYED THAT WAY
FOR A FEW HOURS.
MY GUESS IS THAT'S WHEN ALL THE
PLAYERS' BODIES WERE BEING MOVED
TO HOSPITALS IN THE REAL WORLD.
IF THAT'S WHERE WE ALL ARE RIGHT
NOW, IN HOSPITALS, BARELY BEING
KEPT ALIVE BY MACHINES, IT'S
HARD TO BELIEVE WE'RE GONNA
SURVIVE LIKE THAT FOR MUCH
LONGER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO THAT MEANS IT
DOESN'T MATTER WHETHER WE CLEAR
THE GAME OR NOT ANYMORE.
EVERYONE HERE'S ON A TIME LIMIT.
AND ONCE THAT'S UP...
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SOBS ]
[ CRIES ]
I-I WANT TO -- TO STAY WITH YOU
FOREVER!
I WANT US TO GO ON REAL DATES
AND TO REALLY GET MARRIED
AND FOR US TO GROW OLD TOGETHER!
THAT'S WHY -- THAT'S WHY...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE DON'T HAVE A
CHOICE.
WE HAVE TO KEEP FIGHTING.
&gt;&gt; WHOA.
[ INDISTINCT WHISPERING ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: HEY!
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO WAY.
YOU GUYS ARE COMING, TOO?
&gt;&gt; Agil: THAT'S THE BEST YOU
GOT, "NO WAY"?
HEY, MAN, I SHUT MY SHOP DOWN TO
COME OUT HERE AND HELP GET THIS
DONE.
BROTHER, YOU'RE LOOKIN' AT A
PLAYER WHO'S ABOUT AS
PHILANTHROPIC AS THEY COME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN SEEING AS HOW
YOU'RE SO PHILANTHROPIC, YOU'RE
NOT GONNA MIND IF WE TAKE YOU
OFF THE DROP LIST.
&gt;&gt; Agil: HEY, NOW!
LET'S NOT BE TOO HASTY, MAN!
[ LAUGHTER ]
HMM?
[ ARMOR CLINKING ]
&gt;&gt; CORRIDOR...OPEN.
WELL, HERE WE GO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: FEEL THAT?
THERE'S A BAD VIBE IN HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
[ INDISTINCT WHISPERING ]
&gt;&gt; EVERYONE READY?
THE KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH
WILL BE OUT IN FRONT,
DISTRACTING THE BOSS AND
BLOCKING ITS ATTACKS.
IN THE MEANTIME, THE REST OF YOU
HAVE TO STAY SHARP AND TRY TO
FIGURE OUT ITS ATTACK PATTERNS.
I WON'T LIE.
THIS BATTLE WILL BE HARD.
BUT I HAVE FAITH THAT WE CAN AND
WILL PREVAIL.
FOR OUR DAY OF LIBERATION!
[ CHEERING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE
FINE.
I WON'T LET ANYTHING HAPPEN TO
YOU -- PROMISE.
MAKE SURE YOU PROTECT ME, TOO,
OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
YOU KNOW I WILL.
DON'T DIE, GUYS.
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ CHUCKLES ]
SAME TO YOU, BUDDY.
&gt;&gt; Agil: I'M GONNA MAKE A
FORTUNE OFF TODAY'S DROPS.
NO WAY AM I MISSIN' OUT ON THAT!
&gt;&gt; FORWARD TO BATTLE!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
[ CLUNK ]
[ TONE RESONATING ]
&gt;&gt; NOTHING'S HAPPENING.
WHERE IS IT?
[ RUSTLING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ] UP THERE!
[ SLURPING ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ SOLDIERS GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: IT'S THE SKULL...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: REAPER!
[ SKULL REAPER GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; STAY AWAY FROM IT!
SPREAD OUT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THIS WAY!
HURRY! RUN!
&gt;&gt; UGH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: THAT WAS ONE HIT!
&gt;&gt; Agil: MAN, WE ARE SO DEAD!
[ GROWLING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; AAH!
&gt;&gt; Agil: WE CAN'T EVEN GET IN
CLOSE ENOUGH TO HIT THE DAMN
THING!
&gt;&gt; AAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LOOK OUT!
[ GRUNTING ]
IT'S TOO STRONG!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF WE BLOCK IT
TOGETHER, WE HAVE A CHANCE.
COME ON, WE CAN DO THIS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
ME AND ASUNA WILL DEAL WITH THE
SCYTHES!
EVERYONE ELSE, FLANK IT AND
ATTACK!
&gt;&gt; Agil: YOU HEARD THE MAN!
&gt;&gt; OKAY!
AAAH!
&gt;&gt; Agil: HOLD STILL, BABY!
DAMN YOU!
[ GROWLING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: READY, KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]