[ METAL CLANGING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ HISSES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ PANTING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ Thinking ] IT'S BEEN ALMOST
TWO YEARS SINCE THIS GAME OF
DEATH BEGAN.
I'M STILL GOING IT ALONE,
FIGHTING SOLO ON THE FRONT
LINES.
AKIHIKO KAYABA'S OUT THERE
SOMEWHERE, WATCHING.
I WONDER WHAT HE'S THINKING
RIGHT NOW.
[ SIGHS ]
GUESS I'LL HEAD HOME.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ BIRDS SINGING ]
[ SQUEAKING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU GOT TO BE
KIDDING.
&gt;&gt; [ SQUEAKING ]
[ YELPS ]
[ SQUEALS ]
[ SHRIEKS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: NO WAY!
TH-THIS IS AN S-CLASS RARE ITEM!
HOLY CRAP, THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME I'VE EVER SEEN ONE!
HEY, KIRITO, DON'T YOU ALREADY
HAVE ALL THE MONEY YOU NEED?
I'LL BUY IT, BUT I'M SAYING
WOULDN'T YOU RATHER HAVE IT FOR
DINNER?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SURE. IT'S JUST --
WELL, WHO KNOWS IF I'LL EVER GET
ANOTHER ONE?
&gt;&gt; Agil: SO KEEP IT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S THE POINT?
LOOK, TO PREPARE AN ITEM LIKE
THIS, YOU NEED TO HAVE A
HIGH-ENOUGH COOKING SKILL.
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ SIGHS ]
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IF WE TRY, WE'LL JUST BURN IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'VE GOT MY CHEF.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH, WHAT CHEF?
&gt;&gt; [ CLEARS THROAT ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH -- HEY!
ASUNA'S HERE!
SEEING YOU IN A DUMP LIKE THIS
IS BEYOND WEIRD!
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, SAVE IT!
I CAME TO SEE IF YOU WERE STILL
ALIVE!
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR
THE NEXT BOSS RAID!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M ON YOUR FRIEND
LIST.
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW I'M ALIVE,
JUST CHECK THAT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHATEVER.
NOW I KNOW YOU'RE ALIVE.
ANYWAY, WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
WHAT'S ALL THIS ABOUT A CHEF?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, YEAH -- THAT.
I WAS WONDERING WHAT YOUR
COOKING SKILL LEVEL IS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMM.
TOTALLY MAXED IT OUT LAST WEEK.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT?!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: COOL, HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, IF YOU'RE THAT
GOOD, I NEED A FAVOR.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMM?
[ GASPS ]
Y-YOU GOT A RAGOUT RABBIT?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL TRADE YOU.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS COOK IT UP
FOR ME, AND I'LL LET YOU HAVE A
LITTLE BITE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HALF.
DEAL?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. DEAL.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ Laughing ] ALL
RIGHT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SORRY, PAL.
YOU HEARD THE LADY.
GUESS I'M KEEPING IT.
&gt;&gt; Agil: YEAH, BUT YOU COULD AT
LEAST LET ME TASTE IT, RIGHT?!
I THOUGHT WE WERE TIGHT, MAN!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL WRITE A REVIEW
FOR YOU, BUT ONLY TWO PAGES.
PROMISE!
&gt;&gt; Agil: DAMN! THAT IS COLD!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO, WHERE AM I GONNA
COOK IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. WELL --
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M GUESSING NOT YOUR
PLACE, RIGHT?
YOU EVEN OWN ANY COOKWARE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY.
BECAUSE THE MAIN INGREDIENT IS
SPECIAL, I WON'T HAVE A PROBLEM
IF WE USED MY PLACE THIS TIME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THANK YOU FOR
ESCORTING ME.
YOU MAY GO.
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY, MA'AM.
BUT I CAN'T ALLOW YOU TO GO HOME
WITH SUCH A SHADY CHARACTER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
I DON'T KNOW THE EXTENT OF HIS
SHADINESS, BUT I KNOW HE'S QUITE
SKILLED.
IN FACT, HE'S 10 LEVELS ABOVE
YOU, KURADEEL.
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU IMPLYING I'M INFERIOR
TO HIM?
OH, I KNOW.
HE'S ONE OF THOSE BEATERS, ISN'T
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH? WHAT IF I AM?
&gt;&gt; YOU SHOULDN'T GO WITH HIM,
MA'AM!
ALL HIM AND HIS KIND CARE ABOUT
ARE THEMSELVES!
YOU CAN'T EXPECT ANYTHING GOOD
TO COME FROM SCUM LIKE THAT!
&gt;&gt; HEY! WHAT'S GOING ON?
&gt;&gt; THAT'S LIGHTNING FLASH ASUNA!
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE RIGHT!
SHE'S REALLY CUTE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LISTEN.
I'M SECOND-IN-COMMAND HERE.
I AM ORDERING YOU TO GO HOME.
[ ALL GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ YELPING ]
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OF COURSE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA.
THERE'S HARDLY ANYONE AROUND.
IT'S...REALLY COOL.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF YOU LIKE IT SO
MUCH, WHY DON'T YOU MOVE HERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T KNOW.
THIS FLOOR SEEMS WAY OUT OF MY
PRICE RANGE.
ANYWAY, WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH
THAT GUY BACK THERE?
HE WAS MAD-DOGGING ME LIKE
CRAZY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, HE'S JUST MY
BODYGUARD.
THE GUILD'S NEW POLICY SAYS ALL
HIGHER-UPS HAVE TO HAVE AN
ESCORT.
IT'S LAME.
THE GUILD DIDN'T HAVE ALL THESE
RULES AND REGULATIONS BEFORE.
WE USED TO BE REALLY SMALL.
THEN MORE AND MORE PEOPLE JOINED
AFTER THAT, WHEN WE BECAME THE
STRONGEST GUILD, EVERYTHING
STARTED GETTING WEIRD.
[ BELL CHIMING ]
WELL, I'M PROBABLY MAKING A
BIGGER DEAL OUT OF IT THAN IT
ANYWAY, WE BETTER HURRY!
IT'S GETTING DARK.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. OKAY!
WOW. YOU'VE GOT A KILLER PAD!
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
HEY. HOW MUCH DID ALL THIS COST?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM.
THE ROOM AND THE FURNITURE COST
AROUND 4 MILLION COL.
ANYWAY, MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, SURE.
HOLY MOLY!
4 MILLION!
MAN, THAT'S A LOT OF COL!
I'M SURE I'VE EARNED THAT MUCH,
TOO, BUT BLOWING IT ALL ON A
FLAT?
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: ARE YOU GONNA TAKE OFF
YOUR COAT, OR WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH! YEAH. SORRY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO, THIS IS A
LEGENDARY S-CLASS INGREDIENT.
OKAY!
HOW DO YOU WANT THIS COOKED UP?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I THOUGHT I'D LEAVE
THAT DECISION UP TO THE CHEF.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IN THAT CASE...
HOW ABOUT WE MAKE IT INTO A
STEW?!
"RAGOUT!"
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH THE
DEFINITION OF A STEW.
IN REAL LIFE, THERE'D BE A LOT
MORE STEPS INVOLVED IN PREPARING
THIS.
COOKING IN S.A.O. IS SO SIMPLE.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, IT'S KIND OF
BORING.
THAT TAKES CARE OF THAT!
NOW FOR THE NEXT STEP.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT MAKING A
COUPLE SIDE DISHES.
[ TWINKLING, BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
[ DING ]
[ BOTH SIGH ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'VE BEEN HERE
TWO YEARS, AND THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME I'VE EVER EATEN S-CLASS
FOOD.
I'M SO HAPPY I SURVIVED LONG
ENOUGH TO EAT THAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. ME, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES ]
IT'S SO WEIRD.
SOMETIMES -- I DON'T KNOW -- I
GET THIS FEELING THAT, LIKE,
I'VE LIVED HERE MY ENTIRE LIFE.
YOU EVER FEEL LIKE THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, ALMOST ALL THE
TIME.
IN FACT, THERE'S DAYS I DON'T
EVEN THINK ABOUT THE REAL WORLD
AT ALL.
AND IT'S NOT JUST ME.
THESE DAYS, MORE AND MORE PEOPLE
DON'T SEEM TO CARE ABOUT
CLEARING THE GAME AND GETTING
BACK TO THE REAL WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I NOTICED THERE'S NOT
THAT MANY PLAYERS OUT THERE
FIGHTING ON THE FRONT LINES --
MAYBE 500, IF THAT.
I GUESS THEY'RE USED TO IT.
THEY DON'T CARE ANYMORE.
[ CLINK ]
YEAH, WELL, I WANT TO GO BACK.
I MEAN, THERE'S THINGS I HAVEN'T
DONE YET.
I HAVE TO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
AND WHEN YOU STOP TO CONSIDER
IT, THERE'S EVERYONE ELSE,
RIGHT -- ALL THE PEOPLE WHO
STILL COUNT ON US?
IF WE GIVE UP, IT'S NOT FAIR TO
THEM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM? UH --
UNH-UNH! DON'T GO THERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'VE SEEN THAT SAME
LOOK ON GUYS'S FACES BEFORE, AND
ALWAYS RIGHT BEFORE THEY PROPOSE
TO ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ YELPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM?
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU SHOULD SEE YOUR FACE.
I GUESS YOU NEVER HAD A
GIRLFRIEND BEFORE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EH, WHATEVER!
I'M A SOLO PLAYER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
AND YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT?
YOU DON'T EVER WANT TO JOIN A
GUILD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH --
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I KNOW HOW THE BETA
PLAYERS DON'T FIT IN WITH THE
GUILDS.
BUT...
EVER SINCE WE GOT TO FLOOR 70,
THINGS ARE GETTING MORE
DANGEROUS.
THE MONSTER ALGORITHMS ARE EVEN
MORE IRREGULAR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THERE ARE THINGS A
SOLO PLAYER CAN'T HANDLE --
UNEXPECTED THINGS.
SOMETIMES, WARPING OUT ISN'T AN
OPTION.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, WELL, I'M
PRETTY CAREFUL.
I WORK BETTER BY MYSELF, ANYWAY.
BESIDES, MOST OF THE TIME,
INSTEAD OF HELPING, PARTY
MEMBERS JUST GET IN THE WAY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, YEAH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: M-MY BAD.
EVERYONE EXCEPT FOR YOU.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: GOOD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY
YOU AND ME TEAM UP AGAIN?
BLACK'S MY LUCKY COLOR THIS
WEEK, ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HOLD UP A SEC!
DON'T YOU HAVE STUFF YOU HAVE TO
DO FOR YOUR GUILD?!
YOU CAN'T JUST BAIL ON THEM!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IT'S NOT LIKE WE HAVE
ANY LEVELING QUOTAS TO MEET.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, THEN, WHAT
ABOUT YOUR BODYGUARD?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'LL JUST DITCH HIM!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH --
[ GROANS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
[ LIQUID POURING ]
[ CLINKING ]
[ TWINKLING, BEEPING ]
THE FRONT LINES AREDANGEROUS,
THOUGH.
[ YELPS ]
OKAY! FINE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM!
[ GIGGLES ]
WELL, I SUPPOSE THANKS ARE IN
ORDER FOR THE MEAL, SO THANK
YOU!
>> Kirito: THANK YOUFOR COOKING
MAYBE NEXT TIME --
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT AM I SAYING?
I'LL NEVER GET MY HANDS ON
SOMETHING LIKE THAT AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO WAY!
YOU CAN MAKE ANYTHING YUMMY IF
YOU HAVE THE SKILLS TO COOK!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LOOKING AT THIS
WORLD...
AND SEEING WHAT IT'S BECOME
SINCE WE GOT HERE -- IS THIS
REALLY WHAT AKIHIKO KAYABA
WANTED TO CREATE?
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
WHERE IS SHE?
[ YAWNS ]
[ WHOOSHING ]
HUH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AAH! WATCH OUT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ YELPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANING SOFTLY ]
WHAT IS THIS THING?
HMM. SQUISHY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ WHIMPERS WEAKLY ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
UM, HEY! GOOD MORNING, ASUNA!
WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; WHY ARE YOU BEHAVING LIKE
THIS, MA'AM?
I'M ONLY FOLLOWING ORDERS.
PLEASE, LET'S GO BACK TO
HEADQUARTERS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I WON'T, ESPECIALLY
NOT WITH YOU!
AND WHY WERE YOU LURKING AROUND
MY HOUSE IN THE MORNING, HUH?!
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE A BAD HABIT OF
LEAVING WITHOUT ANY WARNING.
SO FOR THE PAST MONTH, PART OF
MY MISSION HAS BEEN TO KEEP AN
EYE ON YOU IN SELMBURG.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: W-WHAT?!
WHO ORDERED THIS?
IT WASN'T THE COMMANDER!
&gt;&gt; WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, MA'AM,
MY MISSION IS TO GUARD YOU, NO
MATTER WHERE YOU ARE, INCLUDING
YOUR HOME.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
NO, IT DOESN'T, YOU IDIOT!
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
I WISH YOU WOULD BE A LITTLE
MORE UNDERSTANDING ABOUT THIS,
MA'AM.
NOW, THEN, LET'S RETURN TO
HEADQUARTERS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SORRY.
BUT I'LL BE BORROWING YOUR
SECOND-IN-COMMAND FOR THE DAY,
SO YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO MAKE DO
WITHOUT HER.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS, GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR HER SECURITY.
DON'T WORRY -- IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE GOING ON A BOSS RAID.
YOU CAN GO.
SHE'LL BE FINE WITH ME.
&gt;&gt; INSOLENT PUNK!
DO YOU KNOW WHO I AM?!
I'M A MEMBER OF THE GLORIOUS
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH!
A LOW-LEVEL PLAYER LIKE YOU
COULDN'T PROTECT HER!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I CAN DO A BETTER JOB
OF IT THAN YOU.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPING ]
YOU'VE GOT A BIG MOUTH, KID.
SO I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A
CHANCE TO PROVE JUST HOW TOUGH
YOU REALLY ARE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ARE YOU SURE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: DON'T WORRY.
I'LL TELL THE COMMANDER HOW THIS
HAPPENED.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE MOVE TO A SAFE
DISTANCE, MA'AM.
I'M GOING TO PROVE BEYOND ANY
DOUBT THAT I AM THE ONLY ONE WHO
CAN PROTECT YOU!
&gt;&gt; KIRITO'S GONNA DUEL A GUY
FROM THE KNIGHTS OF THE
BLOOD OATH!
&gt;&gt; [ SCOFFS ]
THIS'LL BE FUN TO WATCH!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
[ CHIMING ]
[ CHIMING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
&gt;&gt; HOLY CRAP!
HE DESTROYED HIS SWORD!
&gt;&gt; HOW DID HE DO THAT?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF YOU WANT TO TRY
AGAIN WITH ANOTHER WEAPON, I'LL
BE GLAD TO TAKE YOU ON.
OR WE CAN CALL IT A DAY.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
[ YELLS ]
[ CROWD GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
ASUNA!
I DON'T KNOW HOW, BUT HE
CHEATED!
YOU SAW HOW HE DESTROYED MY
SWORD!
HE MUST'VE USED SOME KIND OF
TRICK!
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY I COULD'VE
LOST TO A PATHETIC BEATER LIKE
HIM!
&gt;&gt; KURADEEL.
AS SECOND-IN-COMMAND OF THE
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH, I'M
RELIEVING YOU OF YOUR DUTIES AS
MY BODYGUARD.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU'RE TO RETURN TO
HEADQUARTERS AND WAIT FOR
FURTHER ORDERS.
&gt;&gt; YOU -- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
DAMN YOU!
[ GROWLS ]
[ GRUNTS, SIGHS ]
TELEPORT -- GRANDZAM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ EXHALES ]
I'M SO SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO DRAG YOU INTO
THAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
ARE YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, I AM.
THE GUILD'S GETTING ON MY
NERVES, IS ALL, MAYBE 'CAUSE
I'VE BEEN SO FOCUSED ON CLEARING
THE GAME, OR MAYBE 'CAUSE I'M SO
DEMANDING OF THE OTHER MEMBERS
IN THE GUILD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I GET THAT.
BUT YOU DIDN'T HAVE MUCH OF A
CHOICE.
THINK ABOUT IT.
IF YOU'D DONE THINGS ANY
DIFFERENT, YOU THINK YOUR GUILD
WOULD'VE GOTTEN AS FAR AS THEY
HAVE?
I MEAN, WHAT DO I KNOW?
I JUST MESS AROUND AS A SOLO
PLAYER, RIGHT?
THE THING IS, IF YOU TAKE A DAY
OFF TO TEAM UP WITH A LOSER LIKE
ME, SO WHAT?
THAT'S YOUR DECISION TO MAKE.
IN MY OPINION, NO ONE'S GOT THE
RIGHT TO COMPLAIN.
SCREW 'EM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WOW!
THANK YOU FOR YOUR OPINION ON
THE SUBJECT!
OKAY!
I ACCEPT YOUR OFFER, AND I'LL BE
TAKING A DAY OFF FROM THE GUILD!
YOU CAN PLAY FORWARD TODAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?!
W-WAIT A SECOND!
AREN'T WE SUPPOSED TO TAKE TURNS
AS FORWARD?!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SORRY!
IT'S MY DAY OFF, REMEMBER?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, COME ON!
[ METAL CLANGING ]
[ ROAR ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SHRIEKING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HAVING SOMEONE ALONG
WHO KNOWS HOW TO FIGHT SURE
MAKES THINGS EASIER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SWITCH WITH ME,
KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH -- YEAH! RIGHT!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ YELLS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SHRIEKS, GROWLS ]
[ SMASH ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO, LOOK.
IS THAT WHAT I THINK IT IS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
WE FOUND THE BOSS ROOM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT DO WE DO?
YOU THINK WE SHOULD LOOK INSIDE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, WE CAME ALL
THIS WAY.
BESIDES, BOSS MONSTERS NEVER
LEAVE THE ROOMS THEY GUARD.
I THINK WE'LL BE OKAY IF WE JUST
TAKE A PEEK.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: O-OKAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HAVE A TELEPORT
CRYSTAL READY, JUST IN CASE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY. ARE YOU READY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
[ DOORS RUMBLING, GRINDING ]
[ DOORS BOOM ]
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
[ BOTH GASP ]