&gt;&gt; IF YOU WANT HER, YOU'LL HAVE
TO USE YOUR DUAL BLADES TO TAKE
HER FROM US.
IF YOU CAN DEFEAT ME IN COMBAT,
YOU'LL BE FREE TO TAKE ASUNA.
ON THE OTHER HAND, IF YOU LOSE,
YOU WILL JOIN THE
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, OKAY.
IF YOU WANT TO SETTLE THIS WITH
SWORDS, THAT'S FINE BY ME.
WE'LL HAVE OURSELVES A DUEL,
THEN.
&gt;&gt; BETTER HURRY, FOLKS!
THE GOOD SEATS ARE GOING FAST!
WHO'S NEXT?!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MY GOD, YOU'RE SUCH AN
IDIOT!
HOW COULD YOU AGREE TO A DUEL?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY! CALM DOWN!
I'M SORRY!
IT'S NOT LIKE HE GAVE ME ANY
OTHER CHOICE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THE OTHER DAY, WHEN
YOU USED YOUR DUAL-WIELDING
SKILL -- I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THAT BEFORE.
THE THING IS, THE COMMANDER HAS
HIS OWN UNIQUE SKILL, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW.
I'VE SEEN IT A BUNCH OF TIMES
MYSELF.
THE DIVINE BLADE.
IT MAXIMIZES HIS OFFENSIVE AND
DEFENSIVE MOVES.
HIS ATTACK IS STRONG, BUT HIS
DEFENSE IS INCREDIBLE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO ONE'S EVER SEEN THE
COMMANDER'S H.P. BAR DIP DOWN
INTO THE YELLOW ZONE BEFORE.
HIS INVINCIBILITY IS WAY BEYOND
THE NORMAL GAME BALANCE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT IF YOU LOSE?
I DON'T CARE IF I DON'T GET MY
LEAVE OF ABSENCE.
I CARE ABOUT YOU HAVING TO JOIN
THE KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, I'M NOT
PLANNING ON LOSING EASILY.
HMPH.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SPECTATORS CHEERING ]
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS, KIRITO.
I DIDN'T THINK THIS WOULD BE
SUCH A BIG DEAL.
THIS IS CRAZY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MAYBE I CAN GET A CUT
OF THE TICKETS?
&gt;&gt; NO.
BUT WHEN WE'RE FINISHED, YOU'LL
BECOME AN OFFICIAL MEMBER OF THE
GUILD.
I'LL CONSIDER THIS YOUR FIRST
MISSION.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] HIS
SHIELD?!
&gt;&gt; YOUR REACTION TIME IS VERY
IMPRESSIVE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, AND YOUR
DEFENSE IS IMPREGNABLE.
[ SPECTATORS CHEERING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOT YET!
GIVE IT TIME!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BE CAREFUL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] NOW'S MY
CHANCE!
[ SPECTATORS CHEERING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...DON'T YOU GUYS
HAVE UNIFORMS THAT AREN'T SO
FLASHY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: ACTUALLY, THAT'S ONE
OF OUR LESS-FLASHY ONES.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU LOOK GREAT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
I'M IN A GUILD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I GUESS IT'S SORT OF
MY FAULT, ISN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, THIS IS A GOOD
OPPORTUNITY.
AS A SOLO PLAYER, I GOT AS FAR
AS I COULD GO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THAT MAKES ME FEEL A
LITTLE BETTER.
HEY. KIRITO?
WHY DO YOU AVOID GUILDS...
AND PEOPLE?
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND MY ASKING.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT BECAUSE YOU'RE
A BETA TESTER OR BECAUSE YOU
HAVE UNIQUE SKILLS, IS IT?
YOU DO CARE ABOUT PEOPLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT WAS A LONG TIME
AGO...
ABOUT A YEAR OR SO.
UP TO NOW, THAT WAS THE ONLY
GUILD I WAS IN.
IT WAS SMALL.
INCLUDING ME, THERE WERE SIX OF
US IN IT.
THEY CALLED THEMSELVES THE
MOONLIT BLACK CATS.
AS PLAYERS, THEY WERE GOOD.
BUT THEIR LEVELS WERE WAY LOWER
THAN MINE.
AND I THOUGHT IF I TOLD THEM
WHAT MY LEVEL WAS, THEY WOULDN'T
HAVE WANTED ME AROUND.
SO I DECIDED TO KEEP MY MOUTH
SHUT ABOUT IT.
AND I JOINED UP WITH THEM.
I'D WATCH THEM MESSING AROUND,
HAVING FUN, AND I GUESS I WANTED
TO BE PART OF THAT, TOO.
THEN ONE DAY --
[ ALARM BLARES ]
I'M THE REASON THE WHOLE GUILD
WAS WIPED OUT.
IF I HADN'T HIDDEN THE FACT THAT
I WAS A BEATER, I COULD'VE
CONVINCED THEM HOW DANGEROUS
THAT TRAP REALLY WAS.
I KILLED THEM.
SACHI...ALL OF THEM!
[ RUSTLING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M NOT GONNA DIE.
GOT THAT?
I CAN'T DIE, BECAUSE...
I HAVE TO PROTECT YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I GOT TO TRAIN?
&gt;&gt; THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU, ME, AND ONE OTHER GUY ARE
GONNA FORM A PARTY.
THEN WE'RE ALL GONNA GO CLEAR
THE DUNGEON ON THIS FLOOR.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH, HOLD ON, GODFREY!
KIRITO AND I ARE ALREADY IN --
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT,
MA'AM.
BESIDES, AS SECOND-IN-COMMAND,
YOU KNOW WE CAN'T IGNORE THE
RULES.
IF HE'S GONNA BE JOINING US,
THEN IT'S MY JOB AS COMMANDER OF
THE FRONT LINES TO TAKE THE KID
OUT AND EVALUATE HIS SKILLS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BUT THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
HE DOESN'T NEED EVALUATION!
HE'S STRONGER THAN YOU!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; KID, IN 30 MINUTES, I WANT TO
SEE YOU AT THE WESTERN GATE!
OOH-AH!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
WE FINALLY HAD A CHANCE TO BE
ALONE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL BE BACK SOON.
THINK YOU CAN WAIT FOR ME?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
JUST BE CAREFUL.
&gt;&gt; HEY, KID!
WE'RE WAITING FOR YOU!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
&gt;&gt; YEP.
LOOK AT IT THIS WAY -- WE'RE ALL
IN THE SAME GUILD, SO I FIGURED
NOW'S A GOOD TIME AS ANY FOR YOU
GUYS TO BURY THE HATCHET!
[ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; ABOUT THE OTHER DAY...
I APOLOGIZE FOR MY BEHAVIOR.
I WAS RUDE TO YOU, AND I --
I PROMISE IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. SURE.
&gt;&gt; ALL RIGHT, LADIES.
TIME TO FOCUS.
TODAY, I'LL BE CHECKING OUT HOW
YOU REACT TO DANGEROUS
SITUATIONS.
SO I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO HAND
OVER ALL THE CRYSTALS IN YOUR
STORAGE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EVEN MY TELEPORT
CRYSTALS?
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM!
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, OKAY.
&gt;&gt; AWESOME!
NOW, LET'S GO CLEAR A DUNGEON!!
&gt;&gt; Both: [ Monotone ] YAY.
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
&gt;&gt; THIS LOOKS LIKE A GOOD PLACE
TO TAKE A BREAK!
CHOW TIME, LADIES!
[ TWINKLING, BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SAY "AH!"
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] WE'VE
BEEN POISONED!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLING ]
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
&gt;&gt; [ Weakly ] THE HELL'S GOING
YOU PACKED THE WATER, KURADEEL.
WHAT'D YOU DO?
YOU BASTARD!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Weakly ] ANTIDOTE
CRYSTALS.
HURRY!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; POOR, SAD, OLD GODFREY.
I ALWAYS KNEW YOU WERE A
COLOSSAL IDIOT.
BUT THIS PROVES YOU'RE EVEN
DUMBER THAN I THOUGHT!
[ LAUGHING ]
&gt;&gt; [ Strained ] D-DON'T DO THIS!
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; NO! STOP IT!
&gt;&gt; HERE'S MY PLAN.
OUR PARTY WAS WALKING ALONG,
WHEN...
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; ...WE WERE ATTACKED BY THIS
GANG OF CRIMINAL PLAYERS WHO
APPEARED OUT OF NOWHERE!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU BOTH FOUGHT HARD, BUT YOU
WERE KILLED IN BATTLE.
IT WAS JUST ME AGAINST ALL OF
THEM, AND, SOMEHOW, I
COURAGEOUSLY AND SINGLE-HANDEDLY
FOUGHT THEM ALL OFF!
[ CACKLING EVILLY ]
[ SHRIEKS ]
[ CHUCKLING ]
YOU KNOW, I JUST KILLED AN
INNOCENT BYSTANDER BECAUSE OF
YOU.
HOW AM I GONNA LIVE WITH MYSELF?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: FROM OVER HERE, YOU
LOOKED LIKE YOU WERE HAVING A
BLAST DOING IT.
WHY THE HELL WOULD A GUY LIKE
YOU JOIN THE KNIGHTS OF THE
BLOOD OATH?
YOU'D BE MORE AT HOME WITH ONE
OF THE CRIMINAL GUILDS.
&gt;&gt; WHAT AN INTERESTING
OBSERVATION.
YOU HAVE SHARP EYES.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
YOU'RE WITH LAUGHING COFFIN, THE
MURDER GUILD!
[ STRUGGLING ]
&gt;&gt; [ SCOFFS ]
THAT'S WHERE I GOT THE SKILLS TO
PARALYZE BASTARDS LIKE YOU.
WHERE'S MY HEAD?
I BETTER STOP TALKING, OR THE
POISON WILL WEAR OFF.
AND WE WOULDN'T WANT THAT.
TIME TO FINISH YOU OFF FOR GOOD!
[ SQUISHING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] THE
POISON'S NOT WEARING OFF!
&gt;&gt; HOW'S IT FEEL?
[ SQUISHING ]
COME ON!
I WANT TO KNOW HOW IT FEELS,
KNOWING YOU'RE ABOUT TO DIE LIKE
A DOG.
WHAT?
IS YOUR TONGUE PARALYZED, TOO?
[ BEEPING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] IS THIS
IS THIS WHERE I'M GONNA DIE?
&gt;&gt; COME ON, NOW!
IT'S YOUR LAST CHANCE TO SAY
SOMETHING.
YOU REALLY ARE GOING TO DIE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING ]
[ FAST BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ STRAINING ]
&gt;&gt; HUH!
WHY DO YOU KEEP STRUGGLING?
ARE YOU AFRAID OF DYING AFTER
ALL?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Weakly ] NO.
I'M JUST NOT...
READY YET!
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
IS THAT SO?!
[ CHUCKLES ]
THAT'S THE WAY I LIKE IT!
[ CONTINUES LAUGHING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; DIE.
DIE!
DI-I-I-I-I-E-E-E-E!!
[ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HEAL!
I MADE IT!
[ Crying ] I MADE IT IN TIME!
THANK GOD.
I MADE IT!
I WAS TRACKING YOUR POSITION ON
THE MAP THE WHOLE TIME.
AND THEN I SAW GODFREY
DISAPPEAR.
I GOT WORRIED SOMETHING
HAPPENED!
BUT YOU'RE ALIVE!
I'M NOT DREAMING, AM I?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO.
YOU'RE NOT.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HANG ON.
I'LL FINISH THIS.
&gt;&gt; UH, A-ASUNA, I-I CAN EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING!
WE WERE JUST TRAINING WHEN ALL
OF A SUDDEN, THERE WAS THIS --
[ GASPING, GRUNTING ]
DAMN YOU!
I GIVE UP! I SURRENDER!
PLEASE DON'T KILL ME!
I'LL LEAVE THE GUILD!
YOU'LL NEVER SEE ME AGAIN!
I PROMISE!
PLEASE!
[ CRYING ]
I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
[ CHUCKLES ]
THE OLDEST TRICK IN THE BOOK,
AND YOU FELL FOR IT, BITCH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPING ]
[ YELLING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPING ]
GOD DAMN YOU. YOU MURDERED ME.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M SORRY.
THIS WAS...
ALL MY FAULT, WASN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M SORRY!
BUT I --
[ GASPS ]
I SHOULD...
[ CRIES ]
...STAY AWAY FROM YOU...
...FOR YOUR SAKE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA...
MY LIFE BELONGS TO YOU.
I'LL GIVE IT UP FOR YOU.
I WANT TO STAY WITH YOU UNTIL
THE END.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AND I PROMISE I'LL DO
ANYTHING TO PROTECT YOU, TOO...
FOREVER...NO MATTER WHAT.
I SWEAR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL DO EVERYTHING I
CAN TO MAKE SURE YOU GET BACK TO
THE REAL WORLD.
ASUNA, COULD I...
STAY WITH YOU FOR THE NIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
OKAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: D-DON'T LOOK.
NOT YET, ANYWAY.
W-WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
GET UNDRESSED.
DON'T JUST SIT THERE!
I-IT'S EMBARRASSING!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
NO, WAIT! I DIDN'T --
I MEAN, I-I JUST --
ALL I WANTED WAS TO SPEND THE
NIGHT WITH YOU TONIGHT, AND NOT
THE, UH --
THE OTHER THING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HM?!
[ WATER DRIPS ]
[ Shakily ] YOU -- Y-YOU --
YOU DUMMY!!
[ SMACK ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY.
WHATCHA SMILING ABOUT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM...
I WAS JUST HAVING A DREAM ABOUT
MY OLD LIFE.
IT WAS WEIRD.
IN THE DREAM I HAD, EVERYTHING
IN AINCRAD, EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENED, AND MEETING YOU, WAS
JUST THAT -- A DREAM!
AND I WAS SO SCARED!
BUT IT WASN'T.
THANK GOD IT WASN'T.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOW, THAT SOUNDS
WEIRD.
DON'T YOU WANT TO GO BACK?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OF COURSE I DO.
I DO!
IT'S JUST, I DON'T WANT MY LIFE
HERE TO DISAPPEAR, IS ALL.
THE LAST TWO YEARS HAVE BEEN
VERY SPECIAL TO ME.
I REALIZE THAT NOW.
LISTEN. KIRITO?
I WAS THINKING...
MAYBE WE COULD LEAVE THE FRONT
LINES FOR A WHILE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M SCARED.
I FEEL LIKE IF WE RETURN TO THE
BATTLEFIELD NOW, SOMETHING BAD'S
GONNA HAPPEN AGAIN!
OR MAYBE I'M JUST TIRED OF IT
ALL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
I GUESS I AM, TOO.
IN THE SOUTHWEST OF FLOOR 22,
THERE'S THIS TINY, LITTLE
VILLAGE BY A LAKE AND A FOREST.
WE COULD GET A HOUSE TOGETHER.
AND THEN...
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AND THEN WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN...
WE GET MARRIED.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]