&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS LOUDLY ]
HOW ABOUT YOU?
FEEL LIKE FIGHTING?
&gt;&gt; NO, THANKS, PAL.
MY MAGIC SKILL'S GONNA REACH 900
SOON, SO I'D RATHER NOT DIE JUST
YET.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AT LEAST YOU'RE
HONEST ABOUT IT.
HOW ABOUT YOU,MISS?
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
GUESS I'LL PASS, TOO.
BUT NEXT TIME, YOU'RE GOING
DOWN!
&gt;&gt; OH.
THEN, NEXT TIME, I'LL MAKE SURE
TO BRING MORE FRIENDS ALONG.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ FLAMES HISSING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, WHAT'S UP WITH
THOSE FLAMES?
&gt;&gt; SHH! THEY'RE REMAIN LIGHTS.
THE PLAYERS YOU KILLED CAN STILL
HEAR YOU.
[ HISSING FADES ]
OKAY, NOWWE CAN TALK.
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU WANT ME TO THANK YOU, RUN
AWAY...
OR DO YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
IF WE BREAK DOWN WHAT JUST
HAPPENED, IT'S ONE OF THOSE
"KNIGHT IN SHINING ARMOR SAVES
THE PRINCESS" MOMENTS.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
>> Kirito: YOU COULDBURST INTO
TEARS AND THROW YOUR ARMS AROUND
&gt;&gt; OH, PISS OFF, LOSER!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ LAUGHS ]
NAH, I WAS JUST KIDDING.
[ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SCOFFS ]
&gt;&gt; NO WAY!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; I WON'T LET HER DO THAT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH! WATCH IT!
STAY OUT OF SIGHT!
&gt;&gt; MOMMY AND ME ARE THE ONLY
ONES ALLOWED TO HUG DADDY!
&gt;&gt; WAIT -- "DADDY"?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHO? WHAT?
N-NOTHING. NO.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
&gt;&gt; NO WAY.
IS THAT ONE OF THOSE PRIVATE
PIXIES?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
SORT OF, I GUESS.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
THEN, HOW ABOUT YOU TELL ME WHAT
A SPRIGGAN LIKE YOU IS DOING
WANDERING AROUND HERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I...GUESS I GOT LOST.
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
OH, HOW COULD YOU GET THAT LOST?
SPRIGGAN TERRITORY'S WAY TO THE
EAST.
[ Laughing ] GOD, YOU'RE WEIRD!
[ LAUGHS ]
ANYWAY, THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
I GUESS I SHOULD INTRODUCE
MYSELF.
I'M LEAFA. NICE TO MEET YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M KIRITO.
AND THIS IS YUI.
&gt;&gt; [ WARBLES ]
&gt;&gt; OKAY, THEN...KIRITO.
DO YOU HAVE ANY PLANS TODAY?
I MEAN, 'CAUSE IF YOU DON'T, I
CAN BUY YOU A DRINK AS...
THANKS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: A DRINK SOUNDS
AWESOME!
AND IF YOU DON'T MIND, I'D LIKE
TO PICK YOUR BRAIN ABOUT SOME
STUFF.
&gt;&gt; LIKE, WHAT KIND OF STUFF?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: JUST MORE ABOUT THIS
WORLD, AND ESPECIALLY...
ABOUT THE TREE.
&gt;&gt; OH. YOU MEAN THE WORLD TREE?
YEAH, SURE.
I MIGHT NOT LOOK LIKE IT, BUT I
KNOW A LOT ABOUT THIS GAME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; THERE'S THIS NEUTRAL VILLAGE
TO THE NORTH OF US.
IT'S A LITTLE OUT OF THE WAY,
BUT WE CAN FLY THERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, BUT WHAT ABOUT
SYLVAIN?
ISN'T THATTOWN CLOSER TO US?
&gt;&gt; YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW
ANYTHINGABOUT THIS GAME.
SYLVAIN IS SYLPH TERRITORY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO?
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE NOT A SYLPH.
IF YOU'RE IN THEIR TERRITORY,
YOU CAN'T ATTACK THEM, BUT THEY
CAN ATTACK YOU.
>>HYAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AS LONG AS I DON'T DO
ANYTHING TO PROVOKE THEM, NO ONE
WILL ATTACK ME.
AND YOU'LL BE THERE, MISS LEAFA.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
JUST CALL ME LEAFA.
AND IF YOU REALLYWANT TO GO
THERE, I'LL TAKE YOU.
I CAN'T GUARANTEE YOUR SAFETY,
THOUGH.
LET'S GET FLYIN'.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...WAIT.
YOU MEAN YOU CAN FLY WITHOUT
USING THE CONTROLLER?
>> OF COURSE. CAN'T YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I JUST LEARNED HOW TO
USE THIS THING, SO I'M STILL
TRYING TO FIGURE EVERYTHING OUT.
&gt;&gt; WELL, THERE'S A LITTLE TRICK
TO DOING IT.
COME ON.
TURN AROUND, BUT DON'T ACCESS
YOUR CONTROLLER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: O...KAY.
&gt;&gt; CAN YOU FEEL WHERE MY HAND IS
TOUCHING YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; IMAGINE YOU'VE GOT VIRTUAL
BONES AND MUSCLES HERE,
SPREADING OUT INTO YOUR WINGS.
THEN TRY AND MOVE THEM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: "VIRTUAL BONES AND
MUSCLES."
&gt;&gt; YEAH! JUST LIKE THAT!
YOU GOT IT!
OKAY, NOW TRY DOING THE SAME
THING, ONLY HARDER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING ]
[ STRAINING ]
&gt;&gt; GO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WH-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-OA!
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ CRASH ]
OH, NO!
&gt;&gt; DADDY!
&gt;&gt; KIRITO! ARE YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAAH!
[ BOTH GASP ]
WHOA! AAH!
HOW DO I MAKE IT STOP?!
[ GROANING ]
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY, DADDY, BUT THAT'S
HILARIOUS!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ LAUGHS ]
WOW! THIS IS AWESOME!
&gt;&gt; I KNOW, RIGHT?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE STARTING TO
GET THE HANG OF IT.
NOW -- FOLLOW ME!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
&gt;&gt; TAKE IT SLOW UNTIL YOU GET
BETTER AT IT.
>> Kirito: DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
WE CAN GO FASTER.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
[ GASPS ]
HUH?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IS THAT AS FAST AS
YOU CAN GO?
>> WELL, DON'T BLAME MEIF YOU
CRASH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ Panting ] I CAN'T GO ON!
I NEED A BREAK!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ PANTING ]
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE THE ONLY PERSON I KNOW
WHO CAN HANDLE FLYING AT THIS
SPEED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE MADE IT!
&gt;&gt; HEY, WE'RE GONNA LAND AT THE
BASE OF THE CENTRAL TOWER, OKAY?
WAIT.
KIRITO, YOU DOKNOW HOW TO LAND,
RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, NOT REALLY.
&gt;&gt; UH...
[ GROANS ]
OH, CRAP. TOO LATE NOW.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAIT -- WHAT?!
YOU'RE KIDDING ME-E-E-E-E!
[ CRASH ]
[ BIRDS CHIRP ]
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Weakly ] THAT WAS
SO NOT COOL.
&gt;&gt; STOP WHINING, ALREADY.
I CAN HEAL YOU.
SOO. FEELAH. HAYDL. ASTALOO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
NO WAY!
THIS IS MAGIC?
&gt;&gt; THE UNDINE ARE THE ONLY ONES
WHO SPECIALIZE IN HIGH-LEVEL
HEALING SPELLS.
BUT THAT'S AN IMPORTANT ONE
ANYONECAN DO, SO YOU SHOULD
LEARN IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DIFFERENT RACES HAVE
DIFFERENT SKILLS, HUH?
DOES THE SPRIGGAN RACE HAVE
ANYTHING THEY'RE GOOD AT?
&gt;&gt; WELL, YOU GUYS ARE GOOD AT
TREASURE HUNTING AND ILLUSION
MAGIC.
NEITHER OF THOSE THINGS ARE MUCH
HELP IN BATTLE, THOUGH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROANS ]
SO, THISIS A SYLPH TOWN.
MAN, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
&gt;&gt; I KNOW, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; LEAFA!
&gt;&gt; Both: HUH?
&gt;&gt; THANK GOD YOU'RE OKAY!
&gt;&gt; OH, HEY, RECON.
&gt;&gt; [ PANTING ]
I KNEW YOU'D SURVIVE.
[ GASPS ]
A SPRIGGAN?!
[ GRUNTS ]
HE SAVED ME FROM THOSE
SALAMANDERS.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; THIS IS MY FRIEND.
HIS NAME'S RECON.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, THERE.
MY NAME'S KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; OH. HI! NICE TO MEET YA.
[ GASPS ]
WAIT! WHAT AM I TALKING ABOUT?!
I TAKE THAT BACK!
YOU SURE ABOUT HIM?
HE COULD BE A SPY OR SOMETHING!
&gt;&gt; [ Chuckling ] NO, HE'S COOL.
I'M PRETTY SURE IF HE REALLY WAS
A SPY, HE WOULDN'T BE SUCH A
DITZ.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GEE, THANKS A LOT.
&gt;&gt; ANYWAY, SIGURD AND THE OTHERS
ARE WAITING FOR YOU AT THE
TAVERN.
&gt;&gt; OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HMM.
ON SECOND THOUGHT, I CAN'T GO
TODAY.
&gt;&gt; HUH? YOU'RE NOT GOING?
&gt;&gt; NOPE.
I SORT OF PROMISED KIRITO I'D
BUY HIM A DRINK FOR SAVING ME.
SEE YOU LATER!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAIT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO --
&gt;&gt; UH...
[ Whimpering ] LEAFA!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IS THAT RECON GUY
YOUR BOYFRIEND?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, ARE THE TWO OF YOU IN
LOVE?
&gt;&gt; NO! WE'RE NOT IN LOVE!
W-WE'RE JUST IN THE SAME PARTY,
IS ALL!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T KNOW.
FROM WHERE I WAS STANDING, YOU
GUYS SEEMED TIGHT.
&gt;&gt; WHATEVER!
I KNOW HIM IN REAL LIFE.
WE GO TO THE SAME SCHOOL, AND
WE'RE CLASSMATES, BUT THAT'S IT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM-HMMMMM.
&gt;&gt; [ CLEARS THROAT ]
ANYWAY, BOTTOMS UP!
AND THANKS AGAIN FOR SAVING ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GULPS ]
[ EXHALES ]
THOSE GUYS IN THE FOREST WERE
PLAYING PRETTY ROUGH.
ARE GANGS OF PKers NORMAL FOR
THIS GAME, OR WHAT?
&gt;&gt; WELL, FOR ONE THING, THE
SALAMANDER AND SYLPH RACES NEVER
GOT ALONG, BUT THOSE GUYS WERE
ORGANIZED, AND THATWASN'T
HAPPENING UNTIL RECENTLY.
I DON'T KNOW.
IF YOU ASK ME, THEY'RE GEARING
UP TO TRY TO CLEAR THE
WORLD TREE SOON.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ACTUALLY, I WAS
HOPING YOU COULD TELL ME WHAT
YOU KNEW ABOUT THE WORLD TREE.
&gt;&gt; OH, YEAH, YOU MENTIONED IT
BEFORE.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I WANT TO GET TO THE
TOP SOON AS I CAN.
&gt;&gt; JOIN THE CLUB.
EVERYPLAYER WANTS TO GET TO
THE TOP.
YOU COULD SAY THAT'S THE GRAND
QUEST OF ALfheim ONLINE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE LIMITED
IN HOW HIGH YOU CAN FLY?
THE FACT IS, NONE OF THE RACES
CAN FLY CONTINUOUSLY FOR MORE
THAN 10 MINUTES AT A TIME.
HOWEVER, AT THE TOP OF THE TREE
IS THE FLOATING CITY, AND IN IT
LIVES OBERON, THE FAIRY KING.
THE FIRST RACE TO REACH HIM
WILL BE REBORN AS AN ADVANCED
CLASS OF FAIRY KNOWN AS ALFs.
AND WHAT'S COOL ABOUT THAT IS
THEY'LL BE ABLE TO FLY AROUND
FOR AS LONG AS THEY WANT.
>> Kirito: THAT IS COOL.
IT'D BE SWEET TO FLY FOR AS LONG
AS I WANT.
[ GULPS ]
SO, HOW DOES SOMEONE GET TO THE
TOP OF THE TREE?
&gt;&gt; AT THE BASE OF THE TREE,
THERE'S A BIG DOME.
THAT'S THE GATEWAY TO THE
FLOATING CITY.
BUT THEN, YOU HAVE TO GET PAST
THE NPCs THAT GUARD IT, AND
THEY'RE SUPER-POWERFUL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEY'RE THAT STRONG,
HUH?
&gt;&gt; LET ME PUT IT THIS WAY -- THE
GAME'S BEEN AROUND FOR A YEAR
NOW, RIGHT?
NO ONE'S GOT PAST THEM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MAYBE EVERYONE'S
MISSED THAT ONE KEY QUEST.
NO, WAIT.
MAYBE IT'S DESIGNED SO THAT ONE
RACE CAN'T REACH IT ALONE.
&gt;&gt; HEY, YOU GOT GOOD INSTINCTS.
FOR NOW, EVERYONE SEEMS TO THINK
IT'S A MISSING QUEST, SO THEY'RE
OUT THERE LOOKING FOR IT.
BUT IF WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER
TO BEAT IT [Chuckling] IT'LL
NEVER HAPPEN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY NOT?
&gt;&gt; BECAUSE IT DOESN'T MAKE
SENSE.
WHY WOULD YOU HELP ANOTHER RACE
WITH A QUEST IF THEY'RE THE
ONES WHO GET THE REWARD?
CAN YOU IMAGINE ANYONEBEING
COOL WITH THAT ARRANGEMENT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN, GETTING TO THE
TOP OF THE TREE IS IMPOSSIBLE.
WHAT'S THE POINT IN EVEN
TRYING?
&gt;&gt; NO ARGUMENTS HERE.
FLYING IS PRETTY ADDICTIVE,
THOUGH.
ONCE YOU GET A TASTE FOR IT, YOU
CAN'T GIVE IT UP.
YOU THINK, "EVEN IF IT TAKES
YEARS, SOMEDAY..."
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT I CAN'T WAIT
AROUND THAT LONG!
[ BANGS FIST ]
&gt;&gt; UH...
&gt;&gt; [ WARBLES ]
DADDY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT I HAVE TO GET TO
THE TOP OF THE WORLD TREE AS
SOON AS I CAN.
&gt;&gt; UH...OKAY.
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M SORT OF...LOOKING
FOR SOMEONE.
&gt;&gt; WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO OFFENSE, BUT IT'S
HARD TO EXPLAIN.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THANK YOU, LEAFA.
ALL THE INFO YOU GAVE ME IS
REALLY GONNA HELP.
&gt;&gt; WAIT.
ARE YOU HEADING FOR THE
WORLD TREE RIGHT NOW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
I NEED TO SEE FOR MYSELF.
&gt;&gt; ALONE? THAT'S CRAZY.
IT'S REALLY FAR AWAY, AND...
YOU'LL HAVE TO FIGHT A BUNCH OF
MONSTERS.
I KNOW YOU CAN HANDLE YOURSELF,
BUT --
[ SIGHS ]
HEY, IF YOU WANT, I CAN TAKE YOU
THERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THANKS, BUT WE JUST
MET, AND I WOULDN'T FEEL RIGHT,
YOU COMING ALL THAT WAY.
&gt;&gt; RIGHT -- THEN MAYBE YOU
ALREADY KNOW HOW TO GET THERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; WHATCHA GONNA DO ABOUT THE
GUARDIANS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL...I'LL THINK OF
SOMETHING WHEN I GET THERE.
&gt;&gt; TOO LATE!
MY MIND'S MADE UP.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
OKAY.
&gt;&gt; SO...
DO YOU WANT TO MEET UP TOMORROW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. SURE.
&gt;&gt; THEN I'LL MEET YOU HERE
TOMORROW AT 3:00 P.M. SHARP.
UM, I HAVE TO LOG OUT NOW.
SO, WHEN YOU'RE READY, YOU CAN
LOG OUT IN ONE OF THE ROOMS
UPSTAIRS, OKAY?
WELL, SEE YOU, THEN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, WAIT!
THANK YOU, LEAFA.
[ BEEP ]
[ COMPUTER POWERS DOWN ]
>>HEY, IF YOU WANT, I CAN TAKE
YOU THERE.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ WHIMPERS ]
TALK ABOUT A WEIRD GUY.
[ SIGHS ]
KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; [ WARBLES ]
I GUESS THIS MEANS GOODBYE TILL
TOMORROW, DOESN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, BUT I'LL BE
BACK SOON.
IT WON'T BE THAT LONG.
&gt;&gt; DADDY?
WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT IF I SLEPT
NEXT TO YOU -- JUST UNTIL YOU
LOG OUT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Chuckling ] YEAH.
SURE.
I DON'T MIND.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU AND ME, WE'RE
GONNA SAVE ASUNA.
THEN WE'LL ALL GO BUY A HOUSE
SOMEWHERE AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; THAT WOULD MAKE ME SO HAPPY.
YOU KNOW, LIVING WITH YOU AND
MOMMY AGAIN WOULD BE A DREAM
COME TRUE.
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S NOT A DREAM.
I PROMISE YOU I'LL MAKE IT A
REALITY.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
GOOD NIGHT...DADDY.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; RIGHT NOW, YOUR FACE IS MORE
BEAUTIFUL THAN ANYTHING,
TITANIA.
THE WAY YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
ABOUT TO CRY, I WISH I COULD
PRESERVE IT AND HANG IT UP ON A
WALL.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR -- PERMISSION?
YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I HAVE NO SAY IN THE MATTER.
YOU'RE THE SYSTEM ADMIN, AFTER
ALL.
&gt;&gt; SUCH COLD WORDS FROM SUCH A
PRETTY MOUTH.
NOW, HAVE I EVER LAID A HAND ON
YOU WHEN YOU DIDN'T WANT ME TO,
TITANIA?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: STOP CALLING ME BY
THAT STUPID NAME.
MY NAME IS ASUNA, SUGOU.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE SPOILING THE FUN.
IN THIS WORLD, I'M KNOWN AS
OBERON, THE FAIRY KING.
THERE'S NOT A PLAYER WHO
WOULDN'T GIVE EVERYTHING TO BE
THE RULER OF ALfheim.
AND YOU ARE QUEEN TITANIA, MY
BREATHTAKING BRIDE.
WHAT MORE COULD YOU ASK FOR?
SO, AS MY QUEEN, AS MY BRIDE,
WHEN WILL YOU GIVE YOUR HEART
TO ME?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NEVER.
THE ONLY THINGS I'LL GIVE YOU
ARE DISGUST AND HATRED --
AND NOTHING MORE.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE A STUBBORN GIRL.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, FOR A WHILE NOW,
I'VE BEEN THINKING -- ROMANCE IS
NICE AND ALL, BUT IT MIGHT BE
MORE FUN...
IF I JUST TOOK YOU BY FORCE.
MMMMM.
[ CHUCKLING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ INHALES SHARPLY ]
&gt;&gt; OHHH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
[ Crying ] STOP IT.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
OF COURSE, MY DEAR.
IT WAS A JOKE.
I'D NEVER REALLY FORCE MYSELF ON
YOU.
I DON'T HAVETO.
YOU'LL START WANTING ME SOON
ENOUGH -- I PROMISE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU'RE INSANE.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU WON'T BE TALKING LIKE THAT
FOR MUCH LONGER.
RIGHT NOW, IN THIS WORLD, TENS
OF THOUSANDS OF PLAYERS ARE
ENJOYING THIS GAME, BUT NONE OF
THEM HAVE A CLUE ABOUT THE TRUE
POTENTIAL OF THE FullDive
SYSTEM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; DID YOU KNOW THAT BY
EXPANDING THE BRAIN'S CONTROL
REGIONS, ONE COULD INFLUENCE A
PERSON'S THOUGHTS, EMOTIONS, AND
MEMORIES?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
YOU CAN'T!
TECHNOLOGY LIKE THAT IS ILLEGAL!
&gt;&gt; OH, BUT YOU'RE WRONG.
IN FACT, SEVERAL COUNTRIES ARE
RESEARCHING IT AS WE SPEAK.
THE ONLY THING STANDING IN THE
WAY IS FINDING PEOPLE TO
EXPERIMENT ON.
BUT ONE DAY, I WAS WATCHING THE
NEWS, AND THERE THEY WERE --
10,000 IDEAL GUINEA PIGS!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; MR. KAYABA WAS A GENIUS, BUT
HE WAS ALSO A FOOL.
ALL HE WANTED TO USE HIS
TECHNOLOGY FOR WAS HIS GAME.
HE COULDN'T SEE THE POTENTIAL
IN IT.
BUT I DID.
IT WASN'T TOO DIFFICULT TO
ADJUST THE ROUTERS.
THE MINUTE S.A.O.'s PLAYERS WERE
LOGGED OUT, I JUST GRABBED A FEW
FROM THE FLOW.
JUST LIKE THAT, I HAD 300 OF MY
VERY OWN TEST SUBJECTS.
MY RESEARCH HAS TAKEN GREAT
STRIDES THE PAST TWO MONTHS.
I'VE BEEN DEVELOPING A
TECHNOLOGY THAT SEEDS MEMORIES
WITH OBJECTS AND USES THEM TO
CONTROL EMOTION.
MY WORK IS ALMOST FINISHED NOW.
>> Asuna: YOU ARECRAZY.
MY FATHER WOULD NEVERALLOW
THAT KIND OF RESEARCH.
&gt;&gt; HE WOULDN'T IF HE KNEW ABOUT
IT, BUT IT'S BEING DONE IN
SECRET -- JUST A SMALL TEAM AND
MYSELF.
OTHERWISE, I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
SELL IT OFF.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: TO WHO?
&gt;&gt; AN AMERICAN CORPORATION.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE HOW ANXIOUS
THEY ARE TO GET THEIR HANDS ON
AND SOON, I'M GOING TO SELL IT
ANDRCT TO THEM FOR AS MUCH AS
I CAN.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THAT WON'T HAPPEN.
I'LL SEE TO THAT.
AS SOON AS I GET BACK TO THE
REAL WORLD, THE FIRST THING I'LL
DO IS REPORT YOU TO THE POLICE.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU WANT TO BET?
YOU'RE IN THE SAME BOAT AS THE
OTHER GUINEA PIGS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HUH?
&gt;&gt; WHAT, YOU HAVEN'T FIGURED IT
OUT?
IF I WANTED, I COULD ALTER YOUR
MEMORIES, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
[ JINGLING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ BEEP ]
I'M ON THE WAY.
WAIT FOR MY ORDERS.
[ JINGLING ]
DON'T WORRY.
THE LAST THING I'D EVER WANT TO
DO IS TURN YOU INTO A PORCELAIN
DOLL.
BUT THE NEXT TIME WE MEET, I
HOPE YOU'LL BE...JUST A BIT MORE
SUBMISSIVE...
TITANIA.
[ BEEPING ]
[ PANEL WARBLES ]
FAREWELL, MY LOVE.
[ GATE SLAMS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ Sobbing ] KIRITO,
PLEASE SAVE ME.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]