&gt;&gt; HERE'S TO US, THE
MOONLIT BLACK CATS.
CHEERS, EVERYONE.
&gt;&gt; All: CHEERS!
&gt;&gt; I GOT ANOTHER.
HERE'S TO THE GUY WHO SAVED OUR
LIVES.
TO KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; All: TO KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, CHEERS, GUYS.
&gt;&gt; THANKS.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, MAN. THANK YOU.
&gt;&gt; YOU SAVED US BACK THERE.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU. THANK YOU SO MUCH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, IT'S COOL.
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW SCARED I
WAS.
AND IT MADE ME SO HAPPY WHEN YOU
CAME TO SAVE US, I...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, WELL...
&gt;&gt; UH, KIRITO, SIR.
I HOPE I'M NOT OUT OF LINE
ASKING THIS, BUT I WAS WONDERING
WHAT LEVEL YOU'RE AT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LEVEL 20.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
YOU'RE AT OUR LEVEL AND STILL A
SOLO PLAYER?
YOU'RE AN INSPIRATION, SIR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: KEITA, I'M NOT YOUR
SUPERIOR.
AND BEING SOLO MEANS I'M ALWAYS
HUNTING ENEMIES OUT IN THE
BOONIES.
IT'S NOT VERY EFFICIENT.
&gt;&gt; OH. RIGHT.
WELL, IN THAT CASE, I HATE TO
SPRING THIS ON YOU HERE, BUT IF
YOU WANT, WE'D LOVE TO HAVE YOU
IN OUR GUILD.
OUR MACE-WIELDER, TETSUO, IS THE
THE ONLY ONE WE CAN PUT OUT
FRONT RIGHT NOW.
AND THEN WE'VE GOT SACHI OVER
HERE.
I WAS THINKING OF HAVING HER
SWITCH TO THE SWORD AND SHIELD.
THAT WAY, SHE CAN FIGHT ON THE
FRONT LINES.
THE THING IS, SHE SAYS SHE'S NOT
SURE SHE CAN HANDLE IT.
IF YOU JOIN US, MAYBE YOU CAN
TEACH HER A THING OR TWO.
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON.
I'M NOT THAT USELESS.
&gt;&gt; UH...
&gt;&gt; SERIOUSLY.
YOU CAN'T JUST PUT ME UP FRONT
AND EXPECT ME TO KNOW WHAT TO
I'D BE TERRIFIED.
&gt;&gt; IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
JUST HIDE BEHIND YOUR SHIELD.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, RIGHT.
EVER SINCE I CAN REMEMBER,
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN A
SCAREDY-CAT.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
&gt;&gt; WE ALWAYS JOKE AROUND LIKE
THAT.
SEE, IN REAL LIFE, WE ALL GO TO
THE SAME HIGH SCHOOL AND ARE
MEMBERS OF THE COMPUTER CLUB.
BUT IF YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
FITTING IN WITH US, DON'T.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED, YOU'RE
ALREADY PART OF OUR GROUP.
RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; Both: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, I'M REALLY
FLATTERED.
AND THANKS FOR THE OFFER.
I'LL DO IT.
&gt;&gt; WELCOME TO THE GUILD.
&gt;&gt; NICE TO HAVE YOU ON OUR SIDE.
&gt;&gt; I KNEW HE'D JOIN.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ HISSING ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SACHI!
GET BACK. I GOT THIS.
[ GRUNTS ]
COME ON, TETSUO! SWITCH OUT!
&gt;&gt; GOT IT!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BEEP ]
ALL RIGHT!
&gt;&gt; CONGRATS, MAN.
YOU TOTALLY OWNED THAT SUCKER.
&gt;&gt; THE ASSAULT TEAM MADE IT
THROUGH TO FLOOR 28.
THAT'S AMAZING.
HEY, KIRITO, WHAT THE HECK DOES
THE ASSAULT TEAM HAVE THAT WE
DON'T?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, ACCESS TO
INFORMATION?
WITH THAT, THEY CAN FIND OUT THE
EASIEST WAYS TO GET XP, AND THEY
DON'T SHARE THAT INFO.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
YEAH, YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
BUT I THINK WHAT REALLY SETS
THEM APART IS WILLPOWER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
I GUESS WHAT I MEAN IS, THEY
HAVE THE WILL TO STICK UP FOR
THEIR FRIENDS OR ANY PLAYER, FOR
THAT MATTER.
TRUTH IS, I LIKE TO THINK WE
HAVE THAT SAME KIND OF DRIVE
EVEN THOUGH WE STILL NEED THEIR
PROTECTION.
THAT SAID, OUR FIRST PRIORITY IS
LOOKING OUT FOR EACH OTHER.
BUT SOMEDAY, IF WE GET STRONG
ENOUGH, WE'LL JOIN THE ELITES IN
THE ASSAULT TEAM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I SEE.
THAT'S A GOOD GOAL.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS.
&gt;&gt; HEY, LEADER, GIVE ME SOME
LOVE.
&gt;&gt; HEY! COME ON!
&gt;&gt; SO YOU REALLY THINK WE CAN BE
AS STRONG AS THE
HOLY DRAGON ALLIANCE OR THE
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH?
&gt;&gt; YEAH. WHAT IF I DO?
NOTHING WRONG WITH SETTING OUR
SIGHTS HIGH.
BUT WE HAVE TO BE LEVEL 30
FIRST.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
>> Kirito: [ Thinking ]I LIKE
THE WAY KEITA THINKS.
IF THE BLACK CATS CAN LEVEL UP
FAST AND GET TO THE FRONT
LINES, HIS IDEALS COULD CHANGE
THE ELITIST ATTITUDE OF THE
ASSAULT TEAM.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
[ BEEP ]
&gt;&gt; I HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT TO
MAKE.
UH...AFTER OUR LATEST HUNTS IN
THE FIELD, WE'VE GOT
200,000 COL.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; WHOA-HO-HO!
&gt;&gt; BUYING A HOUSE OF OUR OWN
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE SUCH A PIPE
DREAM ANYMORE.
&gt;&gt; I KNOW -- WE SHOULD UPGRADE
SACHI'S EQUIPMENT.
&gt;&gt; GOOD IDEA.
&gt;&gt; MNH-MNH.
I'M FINE WITH WHAT I HAVE.
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT FAIR TO MAKE
KIRITO BE OUT IN FRONT FOREVER.
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT
I'M COOL WITH IT.
&gt;&gt; THANKS, KIRITO.
SACHI, I KNOW SWITCHING JOBS
ISN'T EASY, BUT, SERIOUSLY,
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
YOU CAN DO IT. I KNOW IT.
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLING ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ PANTING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: KLEIN.
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ GRUNTS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT'S UP, KIRITO?
THE TRASH MOB'S ALL YOURS, GUYS.
&gt;&gt; SURE!
&gt;&gt; Klein: MAN, IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE SEEN YOU.
WHAT?
YOU DOING SOME LATE-NIGHT
LEVELING OR SOMETHING?
UH...WHAT'S UP WITH THAT ICON?
DID YOU JOIN A GUILD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I GUESS YOU
COULD SAY THAT.
&gt;&gt; IT'S ALL CLEAR!
WE CAN MOVE ON!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SEE YA.
&gt;&gt; Klein: YEAH.
OH, COME ON.
IS IT STILL BUGGING YOU?
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; IT'S KEITA.
SACHI WENT OFF SOMEWHERE AND
HASN'T COME BACK YET.
WE'RE HEADING TO THE DUNGEON
NOW.
PLEASE LET ME KNOW IF YOU FIND
ANYTHING OUT.
[ BEEP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SACHI.
[ BEEPING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
SACHI?
&gt;&gt; KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EVERYONE'S WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
HEY, KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH?
&gt;&gt; WE SHOULD RUN AWAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: RUN AWAY?
FROM WHAT?
&gt;&gt; FROM THIS TOWN.
FROM THE MONSTERS.
FROM THE MOONLIT BLACK CATS.
AND FROM SWORD ART ONLINE, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT SUICIDE?
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
THAT'S NOT SUCH A BAD IDEA.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; HMM. SORRY. NO.
IF I HAD THE GUTS TO DIE, I
WOULDN'T BE HIDING IN TOWN WHERE
IT'S SAFE, WOULD I?
BUT REALLY...
WHY CAN'T WE JUST LEAVE?
WHY DO WE HAVE TO DIE WHEN IT'S
JUST A STUPID GAME?
WHAT'S THE POINT OF GOING
THROUGH THIS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
THERE IS NO POINT, I GUESS.
&gt;&gt; I...AM SO AFRAID OF DYING IN
HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S REALLY THAT BAD
FOR YOU, HUH?
&gt;&gt; I'M SO SCARED.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO GET ANY
SLEEP LATELY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
DIE.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
HOW CAN YOU BE SO SURE ABOUT
THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THE BLACK CATS ARE
STRONG ENOUGH AS A GUILD.
BESIDES, OUR MARGIN OF SAFETY IS
WELL ABOVE THE NORM.
PLUS, YOU GOT TETSUO AND ME UP
FRONT.
SO THERE'S NO REASON TO BE ON
THE FRONT LINES WITH US.
&gt;&gt; YOU HONESTLY DON'T THINK I'LL
DIE?
WILL I MAKE IT BACK TO THE REAL
WORLD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA DIE.
YOU'LL SEE.
WE'LL CLEAR THIS GAME AND GO
HOME SOON.
&gt;&gt; [ SOBBING ]
[ BEEPING ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME IN.
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T SEEM TO GET TO SLEEP.
>> Kirito: IF I STAY IN THIS
GUILD, SHE'LL BE SAFE, AND
WE'LL ALL MAKE IT BACK TO THE
REAL WORLD SOMEDAY.
THERE MUST BE A LOT OF PLAYERS
LIKE HER WHO ARE AFRAID OF
DYING HERE.
BUT STILL, THEY LAUGH AND CRY
AND TRY TO LIVE AS BEST THEY
CAN.
I NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT IT LIKE
THAT BEFORE.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S OKAY.
I PROMISE YOU'RE GOING TO
SURVIVE.
AND NO MATTER WHAT, I PROMISE
I'LL PROTECT ALL OF YOU.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, I'M HEADING OUT.
TELEPORT -- TOWN OF BEGINNINGS.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
I NEVER THOUGHT BUYING A HOUSE
WOULD BE SO EXCITING.
&gt;&gt; DUDE, YOU SOUND LIKE AN OLD
MAN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
&gt;&gt; HEY, WHILE KEITA'S OFF BUYING
THE HOUSE, WHAT DO YOU GUYS SAY
WE GO OUT AND RAISE SOME EXTRA
CASH?
&gt;&gt; OH!
THEN WE CAN BUY FURNITURE!
&gt;&gt; COME ON.
LET'S GO TO A DUNGEON ON A
HIGHER FLOOR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE SHOULD STICK TO
OUR USUAL HUNTING SPOTS.
&gt;&gt; BUT UP THERE, WE COULD MAKE
MORE AND FASTER.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, AND AT OUR LEVELS, WE
DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT.
&gt;&gt; YOU SEE?
I TOLD YOU GUYS THIS WAS GONNA
BE CAKE.
WE MIGHT EVEN BE ABLE TO REACH
THE FRONT LINES SOONER.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
LOOK!
>> Kirito: NO WAY!
A HIDDEN DOOR?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
A TREASURE CHEST! WHOO-HOO!
[ LAUGHTER ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO! WAIT!
[ ALARM BLARING ]
IT'S A TRAP, GUYS! HURRY!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
&gt;&gt; TELEPORT -- TAFT!
TELEPORT -- TAFT!
&gt;&gt; WE CAN'T USE OUR CRYSTALS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEY'RE PROBABLY
BEING BLOCKED BY THE WALLS.
[ MONSTERS GROWLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; TETSUO!
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SACHI!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SACHI!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ CHRISTMAS MUSIC PLAYS ]
&gt;&gt; I HEAR SOMEONE'S BEEN TAKING
RISKS WITH THEIR LEVEL-RAISING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU GOT ANY NEW INFO
FOR ME OR WHAT?
&gt;&gt; NOTHING WORTH CHARGING YOU
MONEY FOR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU GIVE INFO-BROKERS
A BAD NAME.
&gt;&gt; HEY.
THIS WASN'T IN THE BETA TEST.
IT'S A FIRST-TIME EVENT.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW WHAT'S
GONNA HAPPEN?
ALL I KNOW IS THAT TONIGHT, ON
CHRISTMAS EVE, THE EVENT BOSS IS
GONNA APPEAR.
HE'S CALLED NICHOLAS THE
RENEGADE, AND HE'S GONNA SHOW UP
UNDER A FIR TREE SOMEWHERE.
THE MAJOR GUILDS ARE SEARCHING
EVERYWHERE FOR THE TREE AS WE
SPEAK.
HMM.
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO KNOW
WHERE IT IS, WOULD YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MAYBE.
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU THINKING OF GOING
SOLO ON THIS ONE?
>> Kirito: IN THIS WORLD, THE
DEAD CAN NEVER RETURN TO LIFE.
[ BEEPING ]
I HEARD A RUMOR, THOUGH.
IF YOU BEAT NICHOLAS THE
RENEGADE, HE'LL DROP AN ITEM
THAT CAN REVIVE A DEAD PLAYER.
I'M GOING ALONE, AND I'LL
PROBABLY DIE ALONE.
NO ONE WILL SEE ME.
NO ONE WILL KNOW.
NOTHING WILL BE LEFT BEHIND.
THAT'S HOW I'LL DIE.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE A BEATER!
YOU HAD NO RIGHT TO BE WITH US!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S MY FAULT.
MY ARROGANCE KILLED YOU -- ALL
OF YOU.
IF ONLY I HADN'T KEPT MY TRUE
LEVEL AS A PLAYER SECRET FROM
EVERYONE.
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO
BEAT NICHOLAS.
THEN I CAN REVIVE SACHI.
AND THEN I'LL FIND OUT WHAT SHE
WAS TRYING TO TELL ME.
AND IF IT TURNS OUT SHE WAS
CURSING ME, FINE.
I ACCEPT IT.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ PANTING ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: WHAT'S UP?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU FOLLOWED ME?
&gt;&gt; Klein: OF COURSE.
YOU'RE AFTER THE REVIVAL ITEM,
AREN'T YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
&gt;&gt; Klein: DON'T BE RISKING YOUR
LIFE FOR SOME RUMOR THAT COULD
TURN OUT TO BE BOGUS.
MAN, YOU CAN'T BE MESSING AROUND
IN THIS DEATH GAME.
ONCE YOUR HP HITS ZERO, THAT'S
IN THE REAL WORLD, YOUR BRAIN --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SHUT UP.
&gt;&gt; Klein: I'M TRYING TO GET YOU
TO STOP WITH ALL YOUR STUPID
SOLOING.
COME ON. JOIN UP WITH US.
WHOEVER GETS IT TO DROP THE
REVIVAL ITEM KEEPS IT.
NO HARD FEELINGS.
HEY, THAT'S FAIR, ISN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT THEN THERE'D BE
NO POINT.
I HAVE TO DO THIS -- ALONE.
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ GASPS ]
THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE DOING,
KIRITO.
IT'S SUICIDE, AND I CAN'T LET
YOU DIE LIKE THAT.
COME ON!
HUH?
>> Kirito: I GUESS YOUWERE
BEING FOLLOWED, TOO, HUH, KLEIN?
&gt;&gt; Klein: UH-HUH.
IT SURE LOOKS THAT WAY.
&gt;&gt; IT'S THE HOLY DRAGON
ALLIANCE.
&gt;&gt; THEY'LL DO ANYTHING FOR A
RARE ITEM -- NO MATTER HOW
SHADY.
&gt;&gt; WHAT DO WE DO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU BASTARDS.
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ GRUNTS ]
SCREW THESE GUYS!
GET OUT OF HERE, KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO WAY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: LEAVE THEM TO US.
WE CAN HOLD THEM OFF. GET GOING!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BELL CHIMING ]
[ BELLS JINGLING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; [ RATTLING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LET'S DO THIS.
[ YELLING ]
[ ALL SIGHING ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ SIGHS ]
KIRITO! HEY!
W-WHA...?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE.
THAT'S THE REVIVAL ITEM.
[ REVIVAL ITEM BEEPS ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: LET'S SEE.
IT SAYS, "MUST ADMINISTER TO
AFFECTED PLAYER...
WITHIN 10 SECONDS?!"
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF SOMEONE DIES IN
FRONT OF YOU SOMEDAY, MAKE SURE
YOU USE IT.
&gt;&gt; Klein: KIRITO, LISTEN.
STAY ALIVE, YOU HEAR?
I DON'T CARE HOW YOU DO IT.
JUST STAY ALIVE TO THE END.
[ SOBBING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SEE YA.
[ BEEPING ]
[ BEEP ]
SACHI?
[ GIFT BOX BEEPS ]
[ GIFT BOX WHIRS ]
&gt;&gt; MERRY CHRISTMAS, KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; BY THE TIME YOU HEAR THIS,
I'LL PROBABLY BE DEAD.
HOW CAN I EXPLAIN THIS?
LET'S SEE.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH, I NEVER
REALLY WANTED TO LEAVE THE TOWN
OF BEGINNINGS.
AND I KNEW IF I FOUGHT WITH AN
ATTITUDE LIKE THAT, I WOULD END
UP DYING SOMEDAY.
BUT THAT'S NOT ANYONE'S FAULT.
THAT'S SOMETHING IHAVE TO DEAL
WITH.
KIRITO, EVER SINCE THAT NIGHT
YOU FOUND ME, YOU KEPT TELLING
ME I WASN'T GOING TO DIE, NO
MATTER WHAT.
BUT WHAT IF I GOT KILLED ANYWAY?
I KNEW THAT IF I DIED, YOU'D
BLAME YOURSELF.
THAT'S WHY I DECIDED TO RECORD
THIS FOR YOU.
BY THE WAY, I KNOW HOW POWERFUL
YOU REALLY ARE.
SORRY.
I SORT OF PEEKED WHEN YOU
WEREN'T LOOKING.
I WONDERED WHY YOU WEREN'T
TELLING THE TRUTH ABOUT WHAT
LEVEL PLAYER YOU REALLY WERE.
I WONDERED WHY YOU DECIDED TO
FIGHT WITH US.
I NEVER FIGURED IT OUT, THOUGH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHEN I FOUND OUT HOW STRONG YOU
WERE -- I DON'T KNOW -- IT MADE
ME SO HAPPY.
I FELT RELIEVED.
SO EVEN IF I DIE, PROMISE ME
YOU'LL GO ON LIVING.
OKAY, KIRITO?
STAY ALIVE SO YOU CAN SEE THE
END OF THIS WORLD AND FIND OUT
WHY IT WAS CREATED.
FIND OUT WHY A WEAKLING LIKE ME
ENDED UP HERE.
FIND OUT THE REASON YOU AND I
MET.
PLEASE. THAT'S WHAT I WISH.
LOOKS LIKE I STILL HAVE TIME, SO
SEEING HOW IT'S CHRISTMAS AND
EVERYTHING, I'LL SING YOU A
SONG.
[ HUMMING "RUDOLPH, THE
RED-NOSED REINDEER" ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SOBBING ]
&gt;&gt; ANYWAY, KIRITO.
I'M SO GLAD I MET YOU AND THAT
I COULD BE WITH YOU, EVEN FOR A
LITTLE WHILE.
THANK YOU. GOODBYE.
[ GIFT BOX WHIRS ]
[ CLUNK ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]