&gt;&gt; I UNDERSTAND THE SITUATION.
NOW I JUST HAVE EXPLAIN IT TO
THE REST OF THE GUILD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: ALSO, WE'D LIKE A
TEMPORARY LEAVE OF ABSENCE FROM
THE GUILD.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
WHY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE HAVE CONCERNS WITH
THE CURRENT STATE OF THE GUILD,
AND WE NEED TIME TO THINK.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
VERY WELL.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; ALTHOUGH...
I'M POSITIVE YOU WON'T STAY AWAY
FROM THE BATTLEFIELD FOR LONG.
&gt;&gt; Both: UH...
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ LAUGHS ]
WOW, THIS VIEW'S AMAZING!
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
>> Kirito: IT ISPRETTY AWESOME,
BUT DON'T FALL OFF THE BALCONY.
THAT WOULD REALLY SUCK.
[ WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY ]
[ BOTH SIGH ]
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE BOUGHT THE BEST
HOUSE.
>> Kirito: ANDNOW WE'RE TOTALLY
BROKE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ LAUGHS ]
IT'S WORTH IT, THOUGH, 'CAUSE WE
CAN LIVE IN PEACE HERE.
UH...
KIRITO?
WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL...
I WAS THINKING...
DOES OUR RELATIONSHIP ONLY EXIST
IN THIS WORLD?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D
SAY THAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I DON'T GIVE A DAMN IF
THIS IS A VIRTUAL WORLD.
MY FEELINGS FOR YOU ARE REAL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
HUH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF I LEARNED ANYTHING
IN THE LAST TWO YEARS, IT'S
THIS -- TO KEEP DOING THE BEST
WE CAN TILL THE VERY END.
AND IF WE MAKE IT BACK TO THE
REAL WORLD, I PROMISE I'M GOING
TO FIND YOU AGAIN, NO MATTER
WHAT, AND FALL IN LOVE WITH YOU
AGAIN.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ WOMAN CONTINUES SINGING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ Thinking ] USUALLY,
HE'S BRASH AND IMPULSIVE.
BUT HE CAN BE SO NAIVE, TOO,
ALMOST LIKE A LITTLE KID.
[ GASPS ]
[ Thinking ] OH, MY GOD, IS HE
YOUNGER THAN ME?!
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ SIGHS ]
KIRITO...
I LOVE YOU.
LET'S STAY TOGETHER FOREVER.
HUH?
[ SHOUTS ] UNH!
GOOD MORNING, KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM.
MORNING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: D-DID YOU...
HEAR WHAT I SAID?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, I DIDN'T HEAR A
THING.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NOTHING! NOT A THING!
ANYWAY, YOU WANT TO GO HAVE SOME
FUN TODAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
YEAH, YOU KNOW...
DIDN'T WE HAVE FUN YESTERDAY AND
THE DAY BEFORE, TOO?
[ YAWNS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO YOU'RE SAYING YOU
DON'TWANT TO GO HAVE FUN
TODAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
[ SIGHS ]
WAIT, I KNOW A PLACE WE CAN GO.
COME ON!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES ]
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO WAIT TILL WE GET THERE
TO FIND OUT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMM.
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
HEY, CARRY ME ON YOUR SHOULDERS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, SERIOUSLY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, PLEASE!
IT'S NO FUN SEEING THE WORLD
FROM THE SAME HEIGHT ALL THE
TIME.
BESIDES, WITH YOUR STRENGTH
PARAMETER, YOU WON'T BREAK A
SWEAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I MEAN...
I GUESS, BUT...
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
[ SIGHS ]
...AREN'T YOU A LITTLE OLD FOR
THAT, THOUGH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW
OLD I AM.
COME ON, IT'S NOT LIKE ANYONE'S
GONNA SEE US.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
GET ON.
UH...
I-IF YOU TURN AROUND, I'M GONNA
SLAP YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ARE YOU GONNA HOP ON
ALREADY, OR WHAT?
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
GIDDYUP!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
WHOA!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ LAUGHS ]
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
THIS IS SO COOL!
YOU CAN ALREADY SEE THE LAKE
FROM HERE!
>> Kirito: NO, YOUCAN SEE THE
LAKE.
I --
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY, IF YOU WANT, YOU
CAN RIDE ON MY SHOULDERS LATER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LET'S GET A MOVE ON,
HORSEY.
WE'RE HEADING NORTH-NORTHEAST!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ LAUGHS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
[ GASPS ]
IT ALMOST FLEW UP MY NOSE!
[ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE GOT PEOPLE STARING
AT US NOW.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ LAUGHS ]
OUR OWN AUDIENCE.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
GO ON.
WAVE BACK, OR HE'LL THINK YOU'RE
RUDE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOPE, NOT GONNA
HAPPEN.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
DO YOU WANT ME TO GET OFF YOU
NOW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MNH-MNH.
YOU'RE FINE RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHOA!
AAH!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I HEARD THIS WEIRD
RUMOR IN THE VILLAGE YESTERDAY
ABOUT HOW IF YOU GO DEEP ENOUGH
INTO THE FOREST, YOU'LL SEE...
THEM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HUH? SEE WHO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GHOSTS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: Y-Y-YOU MEAN, LIKE,
THOSE IN-GAME, ASTRAL-TYPE
MONSTERS, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, NOT THOSE.
REALGHOSTS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEY SAY THE TORTURED
SOULS OF THE MONSTERS HUNTED
HERE COME BACK TO WANDER THE
FOREST AT NIGHT.
[ BRANCH CRACKS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THE PLACE THE RUMOR
MENTIONS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ABOUT A WEEK AGO, A
CARPENTER HIKED INTO THE FOREST
TO GET SOME WOOD FOR A PROJECT.
HE STAYED SO LONG THAT BEFORE HE
KNEW IT, IT WAS NIGHT.
AS HE WALKED ALONG, HE CAUGHT A
GLIMPSE OF SOMETHING WHITE
STANDING BY A TREE.
[ GHOST WARBLES ]
&gt;&gt; AAH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
[ BELL RINGS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAS IT A MONSTER OR
SOMETHING ELSE?
THE WHITE FIGURE SLOWLY WALKED
TOWARD SOME TREES, AND --
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HEY, LOOK!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, HUH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
AAH!
I WANT TO GET DOWN!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S WRONG WITH
YOU?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
IT'S -- IT'S OVER THERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, YOU GOT TO BE
KIDDING!
[ WHISTLING CONTINUES ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ WHIMPERING ]
[ WHISTLING CONTINUES ]
[ SHOUTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
HOLD ON. [ GRUNTS ]
THAT'S NOT A GHOST!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, WAIT, K-KIRITO!
OH, GEEZ!
[ BELL RINGS ]
IT'S ANOTHER PLAYER!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH...
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING REALLY
STRANGE ABOUT HER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SHE DOESN'T HAVE A
CURSOR.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MAYBE IT'S SOME KIND
OF BUG.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, MAYBE IT IS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT'S A LITTLE GIRL
LIKE THIS DOING PLAYING S.A.O.?
UH...
I GUESS WE'LL FIND OUT WHEN SHE
WAKES UP.
BUT WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE HER OUT
HERE TILL SHE DOES.
LET'S TAKE HER HOME WITH US.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, OKAY.
[ GRUNTS ]
WELL, ONE THING'S FOR SURE.
SHE'S NOT AN NPC.
WE DIDN'T HAVE ANY TROUBLE
MOVING HER HERE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
SHE CAN'T BE THAT.
IF SHE WERE, SHE WOULD'VE GIVEN
OFF A WARNING WHEN YOU PICKED
HER UP, LIKE OTHER NPCs.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE RIGHT, AND
SHE'S DEFINITELY NOT A
QUEST GIVER EITHER.
[ BELL RINGS ]
OUR QUEST LOG WOULD'VE BEEN
UPDATED AS SOON AS WE INTERACTED
WITH HER.
SHE HAS TO BE A PLAYER.
SHE'D PROBABLY BEEN OUT THERE
FOR A WHILE, WANDERING AROUND,
LOST.
THAT'S THE MOST LIKELY SCENARIO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, BUT WHAT WAS SHE
DOING OUT THERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOUR GUESS IS AS GOOD
AS MINE, BUT SHE HAS TO HAVE A
PARENT OR GUARDIAN OUT THERE,
RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
SHE HAD TO HAVE LOGGED IN WITH
SOMEONE FROM HER FAMILY.
I JUST HOPE THEY'RE SAFE.
HEY, DO YOU THINK SHE'LL WAKE
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
IF HER BODY HASN'T DISAPPEARED,
THAT MEANS SIGNALS ARE STILL
BEING TRANSMITTED TO AND FROM
HER NerveGear.
SHE'S IN SOME KIND OF SLEEP
MODE.
I'M SURE SHE'LL WAKE UP SOON.
AND THE SOONER, THE BETTER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH.
[ CICADAS CHIRPING ]
HEY, KIRITO?
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
[ SIGHING ]
I WONDER, DID SHE LOG INTO
S.A.O. BY HERSELF OR WITH HER
FAMILY?
OR HAS SHE BEEN ALONE HERE ALL
THIS TIME?
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
SLEEP WELL.
PLEASE HURRY AND WAKE UP
TOMORROW.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ MURMURS ]
UH...
HUH?
[ CHIRPING CONTINUES ]
[ GASPS ] K-KIRITO, WAKE UP!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ MURMURS ]
GOOD MORNING.
SOMETHING WRONG?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HURRY! GET OVER HERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
[ FLOORBOARDS CREAKING ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU WOKE UP!
THANK GOODNESS!
DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED TO
YOU?
&gt;&gt; MM...
MNH-MNH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY.
HOW ABOUT YOUR NAME?
&gt;&gt; MY...
MY NAME IS...
I THINK MY NAME IS...
I THINK...
[ GASPS ] YU-I.
YUI.
THAT'S IT -- YUI.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THAT'S A CUTE NAME.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME'S ASUNA.
AND THIS IS KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; A-UNA?
KI-TO?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: TRY TO REMEMBER.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING IN THE
FOREST?
AND DO YOU KNOW WHERE YOUR MOM
AND DAD ARE NOW?
&gt;&gt; UM...
I-I DON'T KNOW.
I-I CAN'T REMEMBER ANYTHING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, NO.
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, YOU'RE AWAKE.
CAN I CALL YOU "YUI"?
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
THEN I WANT YOU TO CALL ME
"KIRITO."
CAN YOU SAY "KIRITO"?
&gt;&gt; KI-TO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S KIRITO.
KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; MM.
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
KITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT'S OKAY.
MAYBE IT'S A LITTLE HARD.
HOW ABOUT YOU CALL ME WHATEVER'S
EASIER FOR YOU.
&gt;&gt; MM.
DADDY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: M-ME?
&gt;&gt; AUNA IS...
MOMMY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; MM...
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
OKAY.
I'M MOMMY. THAT WORKS.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
MOMMY!
MOMMY! DADDY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ LAUGHS ]
YOU MUST BE HUNGRY!
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HOW ABOUT BREAKFAST?
&gt;&gt; OKAY!
HMM?
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HERE YOU GO, YUI.
THIS ONE'S YOURS.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, I DON'T KNOW,
YUI.
THIS ONE'S SUPER SPICY.
&gt;&gt; OH.
I WANT THE SAME ONE THAT DADDY
HAS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
IF YOU THINK YOU'RE READY FOR
IT, I WON'T STOP YOU.
YOU ONLY LIVE ONCE, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH...
&gt;&gt; AHH...
[ MUNCHING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; MMM. [ GULPS ]
I LIKE IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WOW, YOU'VE GOT AN
IRON STOMACH.
WE CAN DO A FULL COURSE OF
EXTRA-SPICY FOOD TONIGHT IF YOU
WANT.
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY, LET'S NOT GET
CARRIED AWAY.
I'M NOT COOKING ANYTHING
NUCLEAR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU HEARD THE LADY.
&gt;&gt; YOU HEARD THE LADY?
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SO...
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T KNOW.
SHE'S A BLANK SLATE -- NO
MEMORIES.
IT'S REALLY WEIRD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S LIKE SHE'S A BABY AGAIN.
I JUST...
I DON'T...
[ SNIFFLES, CRIES ]
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I GET IT.
YOU WANT TO TAKE CARE OF HER...
AT LEAST UNTIL SHE GETS HER
MEMORY BACK.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH, YEAH, BUT...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT IT'S A CATCH-22.
WE HAVE TO GET BACK AND CLEAR
THE GAME.
OTHERWISE, IT'LL TAKE THAT MUCH
LONGER FOR YUI TO BE FREE OF IT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I KNOW.
[ BELL RINGS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: FOR NOW, WE'LL DO
WHAT WE CAN.
JUDGING BY THE GEAR SHE'S GOT IN
HER STORAGE, SHE HASN'T BEEN OUT
IN THE FIELD MUCH.
WE'LL CHECK THE TOWN OF
BEGINNINGS.
MAYBE THERE, WE CAN FIND OUT IF
SHE'S GOT FAMILY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ] OKAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO
SAY GOODBYE TO HER EITHER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HUH?
YOU REALLY DON'T?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT
I MEAN, WE JUST MET HER AND ALL.
BUT HAVING HER HERE, IT'S MADE
OUR LITTLE CABIN FEEL LIKE A
REAL HOME.
DON'T YOU THINK SO?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THIS DOESN'T MEAN
WE'LL NEVER SEE HER AGAIN.
BUT LOOK, IF SHE'S GOT A FAMILY
OUT THERE, THEY'RE PROBABLY
WORRIED ABOUT HER RIGHT NOW.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY.
WHEN SHE WAKES UP, WE'LL GO TO
THE TOWN OF BEGINNINGS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT PLACE IS ARMY
TERRITORY.
IT MIGHT BE A GOOD IDEA IF WE GO
IN FULLY EQUIPPED, READY FOR
ANYTHING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, WE BETTER BE
CAREFUL.
&gt;&gt; MOMMY...
DADDY...
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S BEEN FOREVER
SINCE I'VE BEEN BACK HERE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: ME TOO.
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: DO ANY OF THESE
BUILDINGS LOOK FAMILIAR?
&gt;&gt; UH...
I DON'T KNOW.
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T GET DOWN ABOUT
THE TOWN OF BEGINNINGS IS A
REALLY BIG PLACE.
SO, HOW ABOUT IT?
SHOULD WE START AT THE CENTRAL
MARKET?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HEY, KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY
PLAYERS ARE HERE RIGHT NOW IN
THE TOWN?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
GOOD QUESTION.
LAST I CHECKED, THERE WERE 6,000
PLAYERS STILL ALIVE IN S.A.O.,
AND ABOUT 30% OF THOSE PEOPLE,
INCLUDING THE ARMY, LIVE IN THE
TOWN OF BEGINNINGS, SO MAYBE A
LITTLE LESS THAN 2,000?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THEN DOESN'T IT SEEM
A LITTLE DEAD AROUND HERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; LEAVE THOSE CHILDREN ALONE!
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; LOOK, IT'S THAT DAYCARE
BITCH!
&gt;&gt; WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU!
&gt;&gt; UH...
&gt;&gt; LEAVE THEM ALONE, AND LET
THEM GO!
&gt;&gt; YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE WE'RE
DOING SOMETHING ILLEGAL,
BABY CAKES.
WE'RE JUST TEACHING 'EM HOW
THINGS WORK AROUND HERE, MAKING
SURE THEY PAY THEIR WAY.
IT'S ALL PART OF THE ARMY'S JOB,
MA'AM.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S RIGHT.
EVERYONE'S GOT TO PAY TAXES
AROUND HERE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
&gt;&gt; GIN, KAIN, MINA, ARE YOU
OKAY?!
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; HELP ME, SASHA, PLEASE!
SAVE US!
&gt;&gt; THEY JUST WANT YOUR MONEY, SO
GIVE IT TO THEM, AND IT'LL BE
OKAY!
&gt;&gt; WE TRIED, TEACH, BUT THEY
SAID IT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW, YOU DEADBEATS OWE
US A HELL OF A LOT IN BACK
TAXES.
&gt;&gt; YOU NEED TO DROP ALL THE
EQUIPMENT YOU GOT RIGHT THERE,
INCLUDING YOUR ARMOR.
COME ON, HONEY, DON'T BE SHY.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ] NO WAY!
LET ME THROUGH OR ELSE!
STAND ASIDE!
&gt;&gt; HUH?
[ FOOTSTEPS PATTERING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; All: HUH?!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU GUYS ARE GONNA BE
OKAY NOW.
PICK UP YOUR STUFF.
&gt;&gt; UH, OKAY.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT THE...
WHOA! WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
HEY, WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?!
&gt;&gt; THIS IS ARMY BUSINESS, SO GET
THE HELL OUT OF OUR WAY!
&gt;&gt; HOLD ON.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; I GOT THIS.
I GUESS YOU'RE ALL NEW IN TOWN,
YEAH?
'CAUSE WE'RE WITH THE
LIBERATION ARMY, AND YOU DO NOT
MESS WITH US!
[ ALL GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
KIRITO, TAKE CARE OF YUI.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
[ SWORD SCRAPES ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLING ]
WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; AGH!
UNH!
[ SWORD WARBLING ]
OHH!
[ SIGHS ]
[ ALL GASP ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, DON'T WORRY --
IT'S A SAFE ZONE.
YOUR H.P. WON'T DEPLETE, NO
MATTER WHAT I DO.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THERE'S JUST A FEELING
OF GETTING KNOCKED OFF YOUR
FEET.
EVEN SO, A FIGHT WITH ME IS
STILL GONNA SCARE THE HELL OUT
OF YOU.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] NO! NO, DON'T!
AGH!
UNH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
DON'T JUST STAND THERE, YOU
ASSHOLES!
DO SOMETHING!
[ ALL GRUNT ]
[ SWISH! ]
[ ALL MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
[ ALL GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH...
&gt;&gt; AWESOME!
THAT WAS SO AWESOME!
&gt;&gt; OH, I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THAT BEFORE!
&gt;&gt; YEAH, YOU WERE SO COOL!
&gt;&gt; YEAH, THANKS!
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU FOR HELPING US OUT!
&gt;&gt; PLEASE, PLEASE?!
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU SEE THAT?
YOU'RE MOM'S CRAZY-STRONG, ISN'T
SHE?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; THEIR HEARTS...
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
EVERYONE'S HEARTS ARE...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: UH, WHAT'S WRONG,
YUI?!
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI, WHAT'S THE
MATTER?
&gt;&gt; THEIR HEARTS...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YUI, DID YOU REMEMBER
SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; I...
I-I...
I WAS NEVER HERE...
IN THIS PLACE.
I WAS ALWAYS ALONE...
IN THE DARK!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
[ CRACKLING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO, YUI!
&gt;&gt; MOMMY, I AM SCARED!
MOMMY!
[ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MY GOD...
&gt;&gt; MOMMY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI...
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
[ MOANS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT WAS THAT?
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ WOMAN CONTINUES SINGING ]