[ JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ DOOR CREAKS, OPENS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: YO.
YOU'RE EARLY, MAN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'D YOU DO, SCARE
ALL YOUR CUSTOMERS AWAY?
&gt;&gt; Agil: VERY FUNNY.
MAN, AT NIGHT, IT'S OFF THE HOOK
IN HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, I'M HERE.
WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH THAT
PICTURE YOU SENT?
&gt;&gt; Agil: YEAH, THAT'S GONNA TAKE
A LITTLE EXPLAINING.
BUT FIRST, CHECK THIS OUT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: A GAME?
&gt;&gt; Agil: IT'S AN MMO FOR THE
AmuSphere.
IT'S WHAT REPLACED NerveGear ON
THE MARKET.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH.
SO, IT'S A VRMMO...
JUST LIKE SWORD ART.
ALfhaim ONLINE?
&gt;&gt; Agil: UH, ACTUALLY, IT'S
PRONOUNCED "ALF-HEIM."
YEAH, IT MEANS
"LAND OF THE FAIRIES."
&gt;&gt; Kirito: FAIRIES, HUH?
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LAND OF THE FAIRIES?
SOUNDS LIKE A CUTE GAME.
&gt;&gt; Agil: YEAH, THAT'S NOT WHAT I
HEAR, BROTHER.
FOR ONE, P.K.ing's ALLOWED, AND
IT'S GOT THIS HARD-CORE SKILL
SYSTEM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"HARD-CORE"?
&gt;&gt; Agil: I MEAN THE GAME'S NOT
LEVEL-BASED.
IT'S SKILL-BASED.
YOU GOT TO USE YOUR SKILLS OVER
AND OVER TO IMPROVE THEM, AND
COMBAT DEPENDS ON YOUR REAL-LIFE
PHYSICAL ABILITIES.
>> Kirito: THAT IS HARD-CORE.
&gt;&gt; Agil: THERE'S NO SWORD
SKILLS.
OTHER THAN THAT, IT'S LIKE SAO
WITH MAGIC.
WHAT I HEAR -- PEOPLE ARE GOING
NUTS FOR IT, 'CAUSE IN THE GAME,
YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE FLYING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SAY WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Agil: YOU KNOW HOW FAIRIES
HAVE WINGS?
WELL, THE GAME'S GOT THIS
FLIGHT-ENGINE THING, AND ONCE
YOU FIGURE IT OUT, YOU CAN FLY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA.
HOW'S THE PLAYER CONTROL IT?
&gt;&gt; Agil: NO IDEA, MAN.
I DO HEAR IT'S A PAIN TO GET
USED TO, THOUGH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I BET.
HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO CONTROL
SOMETHING YOU DON'T HAVE?
MAYBE YOU HAVE TO USE THE
MUSCLES IN YOUR BACK.
&gt;&gt; Agil: AHEM!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
RIGHT.
OKAY, GETTING BACK TO ASUNA.
WHAT DOES SHE HAVE TO DO WITH
THIS GAME?
&gt;&gt; Agil: LOOK FAMILIAR?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT LOOKS LIKE...
ASUNA.
&gt;&gt; Agil: I KIND OF FIGURED YOU'D
SAY THAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WOULD YOU CUT THE
CRAP?
WHERE THE HELL IS THIS?
&gt;&gt; Agil: ALfheim ONLINE.
THAT WAS TAKEN IN THE GAME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE,
YOU GOT THE WORLD TREE.
AT THE TOP OF THAT, THERE'S THIS
LEGENDARY CASTLE.
PLAYERS ARE DIVIDED UP INTO NINE
RACES.
EACH ONE OF THOSE RACES IS
TRYING TO BE THE FIRST TO GET TO
THE CASTLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY DON'T THEY JUST
FLY UP TO IT?
&gt;&gt; Agil: IT'S ALREADY BEEN
TRIED.
BUT THE GAME'S GOT A LIMIT TO
HOW LONG YOU CAN STAY AIRBORNE.
CHECK IT OUT.
THESE FIVE PLAYERS STACKED UP
BIGGER PLAYERS ON THE BOTTOM.
THEY TRIED LAUNCHING THEMSELVES
LIKE A ROCKET.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
GOOD IDEA.
IT'S INSANE BUT KIND OF CLEVER.
&gt;&gt; Agil: YEAH, WELL, THOSE CATS
DIDN'T EVEN MAKE IT PAST THE
LOWEST BRANCH.
THEY DID MANAGE TO SNAP A COUPLE
SHOTS, THOUGH, AND WHEN THEY
CHECKED OUT THE PICS, THEY SAW
SOMETHING WEIRD.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: A BIRDCAGE?
&gt;&gt; Agil: YOU COULD CALL IT THAT.
AND AFTER ZOOMING IN ON IT AS
FAR AS THEY COULD, THEY SAW HER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
BUT IF IT'S REALLY ASUNA, WHAT'S
SHE DOING THERE?
[ GASPS ]
"RCT PROGRESS"?
&gt;&gt; WITHOUT GETTING INTO
SPECIFICS, YOU COULD SAY I'M THE
ONE KEEPING ASUNA ALIVE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SHIVERING ]
AGIL, CAN I BORROW THIS FOR A
COUPLE DAYS?
&gt;&gt; Agil: SURE. IT'S COOL.
YOU THINKING ABOUT GOING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I GOT TO CHECK
THIS OUT.
A GAME WHERE IT'S OKAY TO DIE
SHOULDN'T BE THAT BIG A DEAL.
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CRAP.
I STILL GOT TO BUY THE HARDWARE
FOR IT.
&gt;&gt; Agil: IT'S COMPATIBLE WITH
WHAT YOU GOT.
THE AmuSphere IS JUST A
NerveGear RIG BUT WITH BETTER
SECURITY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT'S A RELIEF.
&gt;&gt; Agil: THE BATTLE'S NOT OVER
TILL IT'S OVER.
YOU FEEL ME?
GET HER OUT AND COME BACK SAFE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SURE.
AND WHEN I DO, LET'S ALL MEET UP
HERE.
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ CHUCKLES ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
GOD, WHAT AM I DOING?
I'M SO STUPID!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, I'M BACK.
&gt;&gt; HUH?!
HEY, WHERE'D YOU GO?
[ GAGGING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HERE.
&gt;&gt; [ SLURPING ]
[ SIGHS ]
I -- I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA DIE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE SUCH A SPAZ.
THOSE MUFFINS AREN'T GOING
ANYWHERE.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SUGU, ABOUT LAST
NIGHT...
&gt;&gt; YEAH? WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I JUST -- I DON'T
KNOW.
THANKS A LOT.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THANKS TO YOU, SUGU,
I FEEL BETTER.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I CAN'T GIVE UP.
AND I'LL GET ASUNA BACK, NO
MATTER WHAT.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO GETTING
THE CHANCE TO MEET HER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHEN YOU DO, I'M SURE
YOU'LL HIT IT OFF.
ANYWAY, I BETTER GET GOING.
&gt;&gt; WE'RE HAVING THE CEREMONY
HERE ON JANUARY 26th, A WEEK
FROM NOW.
SAVE THE DATE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I NEED YOUR HELP
AGAIN...ONE MORE TIME.
[ BEEPING ]
LINK, START!
&gt;&gt; WELCOME TO ALfheim ONLINE.
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE ENTER YOUR GENDER AND
THE NAME YOU WISH TO BE
IDENTIFIED AS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
>> OH, YOU'RE THE KIRITO?
YOU'RE A HERO. IT'S AN HONOR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; THERE ARE NINE RACES OF
FAIRIES TO CHOOSE FROM.
PLEASE SELECT WHICH RACE YOU
WISH TO PLAY AS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
HUH?
THAT ONE LOOKS GOOD.
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE SELECTED SPRIGGAN.
YOUR CHARACTER'S APPEARANCE WILL
BE DECIDED AT RANDOM.
DO YOU WISH TO CONTINUE?
[ BEEPING ]
YOU WILL NOW BE TELEPORTED TO
YOUR HOMETOWN IN
SPRIGGAN TERRITORY.
GOOD LUCK, PLAYER.
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ WHOOSHING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT?
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
[ GASPS ]
NOW WHAT?
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ THUD ]
AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ MOANING ]
I'M BACK IN ANOTHER GAME...
EVEN AFTER EVERYTHING I JUST
WENT THROUGH.
[ GRUNTS ]
WAIT?
WHERE AM I?
[ GRUNTS ]
HMM?
THERE IT IS.
THANK GOD.
[ SIGHS ]
[ BEEP ]
OKAY, WHERE'S THE STATUS WINDOW?
HUH?
WHAT IS THIS?
OH, PLEASE DON'T BE A BUG.
[ GASPS ]
IT'S ALL MY SKILLS AND STATS
FROM SAO.
THE HELL'S GOING ON?
AM I BACK INSIDE SAO?
[ BEEP ]
[ GASPS ]
UH-OH.
OH, CRAP.
COME ON.
PLEASE BE HERE.
[ GASPS ]
[ BEEP ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, YUI.
IT'S ME.
YOU REMEMBER?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
I DO. I REMEMBER YOU, DADDY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
MOMMY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ Chuckling ] YOU MUST
BE HUNGRY.
HOW ABOUT BREAKFAST?
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
UH, MMM. MMM.
MMM, MMM, MMM.
[ GULPS ]
I LIKE IT.
MOMMY...DADDY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; DADDY!
DADDY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE BACK.
IT'S A MIRACLE.
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO, DO YOU KNOW WHERE
YOU ARE OR WHAT'S GOING ON?
&gt;&gt; MNH-MNH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
WELL, WE'RE NOT IN SAO ANYMORE.
WE'RE IN A TOTALLY DIFFERENT
GAME NOW.
IT'S CALLED ALfheim ONLINE.
&gt;&gt; I NEED A FEW SECONDS TO
ASSESS IT.
FROM WHAT I CAN TELL, THIS WORLD
HAS BEEN COPIED FROM THE
SWORD ART ONLINE SERVERS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: REALLY?
&gt;&gt; YES.
THE ENGINE, PROGRAMMING, AND
GRAPHICS FORMAT ARE EXACTLY THE
SAME.
THE CARDINAL SYSTEM NEEDS
UPDATING, BUT THAT'S THE ONLY
THING THAT STICKS OUT TO ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
THAT MAKES SENSE, 'CAUSE ARGUS
WAS THE COMPANY RUNNING SAO.
THEY FOLDED, AND RCT TOOK OVER.
YEAH.
AND IF RCT HAS ALREADY GOT ALL
OF ARGUS' TECHNOLOGY, IT FIGURES
THEY'D PORT IT OVER...
ALTHOUGH, WHEN I CHECKED, I
STILL HAD MY OLD SKILLS AND
STATS.
&gt;&gt; STRANGE.
I'LL TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR DATA
AND SEE WHAT I FIND.
VERY INTERESTING.
YOU'RE RIGHT, THIS IS THE SAME
CHARACTER DATA YOU USED WHEN YOU
WERE IN SAO.
THE FORMATTING FOR SAVED DATA IS
ALMOST IDENTICAL.
WHATEVER SKILLS YOU HAD THAT
WERE SIMILAR IN BOTH GAMES WERE
PORTED OVER AND MERGED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
THAT'S WHY MY DUAL-WIELDING
SKILL IS GONE.
&gt;&gt; NOT JUST THAT.
ALL YOUR ITEMS SEEM TO BE LOST,
TOO.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO DELETE THEM
BEFORE THE ERROR-DETECTION
PROGRAM FINDS OUT ABOUT IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I BETTER.
[ GASPS ]
HMM.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; HMM?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, WHAT AM I GONNA
DO ABOUT MY SKILL LEVEL?
&gt;&gt; NO ONE ELSE CAN SEE THEM.
WELL, NO ONE EXCEPT THE
GAME MASTER, AND AS LONG AS HE
DOESN'T, YOU SHOULD BE OKAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. AWESOME.
HMM.
I GUESS I'M NOT A BEATER
ANYMORE.
JUST A PLAIN OLD CHEATER NOW.
HOW ARE YOU BEING IDENTIFIED BY
THE SYSTEM?
&gt;&gt; LET'S SEE.
IT'S CLASSIFYING ME AS A
PLAYER-SUPPORT PROGRAM.
IN THE WORLD OF THE GAME, I'M A
NAVIGATION PIXIE.
[ TWINKLE! ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
HEY!
[ TWINKLE! ]
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
THIS IS WHAT I LOOK LIKE AS A
PIXIE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA.
&gt;&gt; NO, DADDY!
THAT'S ANNOYING!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU HAD ADMIN
PRIVILEGES IN SAO.
DO YOU STILL HAVE THEM?
&gt;&gt; NO.
THE SYSTEM WILL ONLY ALLOW ME TO
ACCESS THE WIDE-AREA MAPS AND
THE REFERENCE DATABASE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
LISTEN, YUI...
I THINK YOUR MOMMY MIGHT BE
STUCK IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
&gt;&gt; MOMMY? REALLY?!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, SHE'S STUCK?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AFTER SAO WAS
CLEARED, ASUNA NEVER WOKE UP IN
THE REAL WORLD.
I FOUND OUT SHE WAS SEEN IN
ALfheim.
THERE'S A PICTURE, BUT IT'S TOO
BLURRY TO TELL.
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, I GOT A PRETTY
GOOD IDEA WHERE SHE MIGHT BE.
IT'S SOMETHING CALLED THE
WORLD TREE.
I THINK IT'S OVER THERE.
&gt;&gt; MOMMY'S THERE? REALLY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, HANG ON A SECOND.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO START THE GAME
IN A TOWN IN SPRIGGAN TERRITORY.
SO, HOW COME I ENDED UP HERE, IN
THIS FOREST, INSTEAD?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW.
YOUR LOCATION DATA MAY BE
CORRUPTED.
OR PERHAPS THERE WAS SOME
INTERFERENCE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EITHER WAY, IT
WOULD'VE BEEN NICE IF THE GAME
DROPPED ME A LITTLE CLOSER TO
THE WORLD TREE.
WELL, LET'S GO.
[ TWINKLE! ]
WOW!
THESE ARE MY WINGS, HUH?
HOW DO I FLY WITH THEM?
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE TO ACCESS YOUR
CONTROLLER FIRST.
RAISE YOUR LEFT HAND.
THEN, POSITION YOUR FINGERS LIKE
YOU'RE GRABBING SOMETHING.
PULL IT TOWARD YOURSELF TO
ELEVATE.
PUSH IT AWAY TO DESCEND.
AND MOVE IT LEFT OR RIGHT TO
TURN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
[ GASPS ] OH!
&gt;&gt; HOLD DOWN THE BUTTON TO
ACCELERATE.
TO DECELERATE, JUST EASE UP ON
IT A LITTLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPING ]
AS LONG AS YOUR WINGS ARE
SHINING, YOU CAN STAY AIRBORNE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; BUT YOU CAN'T FLY FOREVER.
AFTER A WHILE, YOU'LL NEED TO
REST YOUR WINGS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ LAUGHING ]
THIS IS GREAT!
I THINK I'VE GOT IT DOWN.
DO ME A FAVOR.
SCAN THE MAP AND SEE WHERE THE
NEAREST TOWN IS.
&gt;&gt; THERE'S ONE IN
SYLPH TERRITORY, WEST OF HERE.
IT'S A TOWN CALLED SYLVAIN.
IT'S THE CLOSEST ONE.
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SOMETHING WRONG?
&gt;&gt; THERE ARE OTHER PLAYERS NEAR
HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
&gt;&gt; HEY! WAIT UP FOR ME!
LEAFA!
&gt;&gt; HURRY IT UP, RECON!
A LITTLE FURTHER AND WE'LL BE IN
SYLPH TERRITORY!
[ GASPS ]
WATCH OUT, RECON!
[ BOTH GASPING ]
GEEZ! THEY NEVER GIVE UP!
OKAY, THEN. PREPARE FOR BATTLE!
&gt;&gt; OHH! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
SIGURD AND THE OTHERS ARE
ALREADY THERE BY NOW!
&gt;&gt; I'LL KEEP THESE GUYS BUSY.
YOU TRY TO KNOCK ONE OF THEM
DOWN, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; IF YOU SAY SO.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
SHOW ME HOW USEFUL YOU CAN BE.
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; AAH! OH!
&gt;&gt; HYAH!
&gt;&gt; DAMN IT!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
[ SWORDS CLANGING ]
&gt;&gt; WE CAN WIN THIS!
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; AAH!
&gt;&gt; IDIOT! DON'T STOP!
&gt;&gt; UGH!
SORRY!
&gt;&gt; RECON!
[ WHOOSHING ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; HYAH!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
AAH!
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; SORRY ABOUT THIS.
WE'RE ON A MISSION, THOUGH.
GIVE UP YOUR MONEY AND ITEMS,
AND WE'LL LET YOU GO.
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE ACTING LIKE SUCH A
GENTLEMAN FOR, KAGEMUNE?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, WE HAVEN'T FOUGHT A
CHICK IN FOREVER.
COME ON, LET'S WASTE HER!
&gt;&gt; [ SCOFFS ]
GO ON, TRY IT, BUT I'M TAKING
ONE OF YOU WITH ME.
WHOEVER IS NOT AFRAID OF DYING,
COME ON!
STEP UP AND GET SOME.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE A STUBBORN GIRL.
SUIT YOURSELF.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAAH!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH!
[ GRUNTING ]
OHH.
[ GRUNTS ]
DAMN.
GOT TO WORK ON THOSE LANDINGS.
&gt;&gt; UH...
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
GO! GET OUT OF HERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WOULD SOMEONE TELL ME
WHY THREE BIG GUYS ARE FIGHTING
ONE SINGLE GIRL?
THAT'S PRETTY UNCOOL, IF YOU ASK
&gt;&gt; WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
&gt;&gt; BETTER GET YOUR ASS OUT OF
HERE, NEWB, FAST!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; YOU ASKED FOR IT.
GET READY TO DIE!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; HYAH!
[ TWINKLE! ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?
[ GASPS ]
[ METAL CREAKING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SEE YA.
&gt;&gt; AAAH!
&gt;&gt; Both: UGH!
UGH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EXCUSE ME.
HATE TO INTERRUPT, BUT YOU MIND
IF I TAKE CARE OF THIS?
&gt;&gt; UH, I GUESS, IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO.
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY WERE GONNA
LET YOU WALK OUT OF HERE ALIVE
ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN SIT BACK AND LET
ME AT THEM.
[ SHING! ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?
WHERE'D HE GO?
AAH!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; UH, UH...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
OKAY, WHO'S NEXT?
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]