Marry me.
I will make you happy, Chtholly.
You're looking particularly smug.
Smug, me?
I look smug?
I assume something good must have happened?
Uh! Well, I guess so, yeah.
At least I think so.
You know, you're just like an open book.
Hey, Rhan.
What do you think finding happiness...
What do you think it's all about?
To begin with,
happiness means different things to different people.
To some, it means having food on their table.
To others, it means books on their shelf.
Some believe that doing one's very best
is what truly matters in the long run.
And some are only content if they
can overcome hurdles in their path.
Some take joy in witnessing and
nourishing the happiness of others.
While some, sadly, revel in others' sorrow.
I gotta say, I didn't expect such a long
response. You're giving me a joy thesis.
That said, most creatures do
not realize this about themselves.
They do not know what, in
actuality, will bring them happiness.
Yet, they still talk about their desire to
find happiness as if they knew where to look.
One day, such people may learn
that they were blessed all along,
but they will never realize it when they're happy.
In my opinion, to know the truth, one
must simply listen to their own heart.
Make sense?
I hope that successfully answered your
question and made you somewhat happy.
Oh, god. Why?
Why is everything so awkward?
How did I pursue him like I did up until yesterday?
This is so hard!
Maybe I could ask to kiss him again.
Would he accept this time?
Yeah, surely he would. I mean, he did propose to me.
We're like a couple now... Probably.
I'll give it a shot later.
Yeah, I'm gonna go for it.
I have a plan!
What was that look about?
Oh, quit blushing! You're embarrassing yourself!
So, listen.
What is it?
About yesterday's, um, well, you-know-what.
Oh, yeah.
I, um...
I just want you to know I fully intend to keep my promise.
I'll spend the rest of my life
making you happ... Oh! There you are!
Look left, you crazy kids!
It's okay, Willem.
I made a promise to you, too. Remember?
I'll be with you forever.
Hey Boss,
where do you want me to put this?
Oh, over there is fine.
Sorry to keep you waiting, but I'm here now.
What is this?
Supposedly, they're the forces
of the visitor Elq Hrqstn.
Elq Hrqstn?
According to legend, this
world was once home to gods.
But they attacked the humans in a bid to wipe them out.
The one at the top is Carminelake,
the middle one is Jadenail,
and the last one is, uh...
He's Eboncandle.
Yeah, that's the one!
Ha, ha, ha! Of course you'd know.
Of course.
After all, I did personally fight him.
Uh?
Come on, Willem you're tryin' too hard.
You don't have to be like that with us.
It's true.
I should have asked them what happened with the war.
After we took each other out, I mean.
Yeah, whatever you say, friend, but for
now, let me lead you to your destination.
Hey! Look, Pops is here!
Sis, hurry! Pops has finally made it back to us!
Can I say "I'm home" now?
Doesn't feel right anymore.
Ship sailing the starry sky.
Light in the palm of the hand.
Clay doll walking on all fours.
Something feels weird.
It's like I'm being called.
Underground?
What is it?
Everything okay there, missy?
What is that thing?!
It's a monster!
Yes, that much is fairly obvious, you fool!
What I want to know is what the-- Come back here!
Oh, no.
Why did you leave? This is so terrifying.
Timere?
Son of a--
Looks like we fell pretty far.
Apparently, there's been a massive cave below Gomag City,
but what is it for?
Chtholly...?
Willem, why are you...?
What were you thinking?!
You know your body can't handle this kind of strain!
I'm fine, don't worry about it.
Hey, you all right?
Think so.
I have a feeling we need to get out of here, and fast.
Yeah, but how?
This looks to be the underground ruins where
that idiotic officer sent out a squad to scavenge.
You see all those markers that lead down that way?
Hopefully, they'll direct us to the exit.
Course, that's assuming the
path hasn't caved in somewhere.
Not long ago, I could've just flown out.
There's no need to worry, I promise to keep you safe.
Well, I'd rather be the one keeping you safe.
I understand, but guardians have the right
as well as the duty to guard their charges, don't they?
Who are you calling your charge?
I thought I was your, uh, you know, your um...
Oh, you know.
Oh... What is that stench?
Oh, yep. Found it.
These soldiers are the excavations squad, right?
Yeah, poor guys. This was terrible.
These wounds are definitely a timere's work.
You can tell because of how savage they are.
That thing's hangin' around nearby, we're in big trouble.
Timere.
One of the beasts that destroyed the world.
If they were really humans all along,
then the monster that did this...
Elq.
Hm?
Yes, yes.
You want me to go there?
All right, then.
Chtholly?
What's wrong?
I'm on my way.
Hey! Chtholly!
Missy! Oh, come on!
Do you know what she's doing?
Men, prepare to take off immediately!
We can't, sir!
Shaft Three's been done in.
I am a veteran First-Grade Technical Officer!
I can fix that in my sleep!
I'm telling you to be ready to leave once I'm done!
Is that understood?!
Right! Yes, sir!
Hey! Welcome back!
Same to you.
Where's Rhan?
She's keeping watch over there.
Can we call it a day now? Haven't we taken out enough?
You really believe that's possible?
No, I just want this nightmare
to end before more people get hurt.
Won't be over for a while, though.
Worried about Chtholly, Grick, and that T.O...
I hope they get back in one piece.
Don't be stupid!
Leave that crap behind!
But I went to all the trouble to find it!
We don't have time for this nonsense,
our lives are far more important!
I'm not saying they're not...
"Our lives are far more important," huh?
Wise words, I'd say.
Not that I actually understand them.
Get some rest. I bet you're tired.
I'll take care of this.
Got a job to do.
Lives to guard, futures to save, and all that.
Same old, same old, but I love it!
Chtholly, wait!
Chtholly!
Please, stop. What are you doing?
Willem, is that you?
Yes, it's me, but you need to focus right now.
Don't lose sight of yourself!
Uh! Will ya look at that.
Amazing. I never thought I'd get the chance to
see two of these within a borgle's short lifespan.
Oh, ouch!
Poor thing's been stabbed clean through.
Is that Seniorious's hex?
Is who what?
You know how fairy tales have curses that
can turn people into frogs and things like that?
This is the same idea.
A curse that can turn anyone,
god or immortal, into a corpse.
A world-altering ability exclusive
to the holy sword Seniorious.
If it was used on her, then there's no
way she was just an ordinary little girl.
Uh?
Chtholly?
Chtholly!
We gotta go!
Grab a hold of your girl and run!
I got it.
Listen to me, Chtholly, we're leaving.
Please, try to stay in control of yourself.
Hang on.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Willem...
I'm here, right here.
I'll always be here with you!
I can't... I don't know...
Chtholly?
Talk to me. What is it?
This way! Willem hurry, we're running out of time!
Chtholly?
Please, Chtholly, say something!
Chtholly!
Ah! Damn it, even the pressure valves are blown!
What, they are?
Is the ship done for then?
Hell, no!
I am not about to die here!
I want you to bring me every last
thing I could use to repair this bastard!
I never managed to bring happiness
to anyone in my entire life.
That's why I wanted... wanted to make you girls...
All I wanted to do was to make you happy.
But I just... I...
Why does everything always have to end up like this?
You okay, missy?
I just want to be in there with them.
Of course you do.
I'm sure that would make them feel a lot better.
I'm sorry. I wish I could've
done more than just bring her back.
It's all right. This wasn't anyone's
fault, so there isn't anyone to blame.
We all knew the ice we were walking on with her was thin.
Where am I?
I'm doing this for one reason.
It's for my love.
For love?
For that reason alone, I have come to slay a god.
And yes, I fully realize I'm here on a fool's errand.
But I have no other choice.
This man, he's the walking definition of stupid.
So I have to move on these idiotic ideas
before he can think them up for himself.
Because, Willem's a complete and utter moron.
Time to say goodbye.
Rest in peace!
Uh?
What was that?
Welcome back to me, Chtholly.
I do know you. We've met before.
Do you wanna know something?
Because I have something I want you to know!
Tell me.
A long, long time ago, a race called
"humanity" was attempting to destroy the world.
To prevent the destruction, the Poteaus,
three gods who were watching over the world,
decided to lead an army in
order to wipe out all of humanity.
Sadly, they failed.
A human brave killed their master before they
could overpower their enemy to save the world.
No one could stop the humans now.
They turned into beasts and obliterated everything.
I bet you're wondering who their master was.
Her name was Elq Hrqstn!
She was the last of the visitors,
and she died as a child.
You're Elq. That's your name, isn't it?
Uh-huh, but it is also the name of your soul.
Fairies like you are created
from the souls of children
who were too young to realize they were dead.
Ever since the day Lillia arrived
and killed me, I've been dreaming.
I dream of being like her,
I dream of being as brave and as strong as her.
And I dream of putting my life on the
line and fighting for the people I love.
Is that what I am?
Yes, that is what all Leprechauns are.
What will happen to me, then?
You already know, do you not?
No dream is able to last forever.
And dreams are so quickly forgotten,
until nothing at all remains of them?
It's all right.
You made it back here to me just in time.
Rhan!
Thank you. I'm so exhausted.
Would you like to switch out
with Nephren for a short time?
Nah, she's kinda preoccupied.
Besides, I figure we've probably taken
out all the timere in the area by now.
By the way, Nopht, how is your body currently feeling?
Oh, it's super great
for some crazy reason,
and what's more, Desperatio's doing
everything exactly the way I want, too!
Same for me.
In which case, could what we're experiencing somehow
be positive effects from that rather dubious massage?
Oh...
Meaning, that man
wasn't simply touching us like
he did for perverted reasons.
Wow, talk about mean.
You really do hate that guy, don't you?
I just don't accept him as readily.
It appears that our break time has been cut short.
No problem, here.
Given the shape I'm in today, I
could take on another 10 or 20, easily!
How about a hundred or two, instead?
I think that might be a little too much.
Is that so?
Unfortunate.
Huh?
Get ready.
At this point, we must prepare for the very worst.
Yep, certainly looks that way.
This whole thing is the very worst.
In the end, I failed to do it.
You failed to do what?
Talk to her.
I wanted to communicate with Chtholly again.
I'd have even settled for a fight.
I was given yet another chance, and I wasted it.
I see.
All right.
Emergency repairs done!
Power up the circuits, now!
Roger that.
Powering up the circuits!
Ready and aim!
Fire!
Captain!
Stay back.
We are the only ones who can kill these beasts.
B-But how?
Don't ask.
Know this battlefield is ours and kill or be killed
applies to us. This fight is no longer your fight.
Oh god.
You hurt yourself protecting us.
Are you all right?
You need to go.
Run.
I won't be able to hold them off much longer.
Go, now.
Three is too damaged for
it to stay on the grid!
Two and six are fine, though!
Reroute the load to them!
Oh, for cryin' out loud, I've only ever flown small ships!
Can you give a guy a break?
Chtholly.
I don't...
I don't know what to say.
You don't?
Maybe that's because you never
really cared that much about her.
Remember how you couldn't stop Lillia from fighting?
All you did was use another
wielder of Seniorious as a substitute.
You couldn't keep your promise to Almaria, either.
So you made a different promise with this girl instead.
You never really saw Chtholly for who she was,
and you always treated her like a child.
That way you'd have an excuse to discount her.
You're wrong! I wanted her to...
You need to face it.
You lied to them.
I will make you happy, Chtholly.
I failed.
I fell short of my promise... again.
And now you.
Yet another beast?
Welcome, then, but
you should know,
right now, I need someone to take some rage out on.
There's barely anything "you" left of you.
Your mind and body have been almost entirely replaced.
They've been replaced by my body and mind, naturally.
I'm glad you made it here before
you disappeared completely, though.
Your joys, and your sorrows,
oh, and your love for someone.
I know you must surely still remember those things,
just a little bit? You do, do you not?
Yes, but only a very little bit.
Yay! That must be a relief.
Everything's all right, and you're still Chtholly!
Will... em...
Final Episode: Chtholly.