[bell tolls]
[LIZARD LADY 4A whimpers]
[LIZARD MAN 4A growls]
[LIZARD LADY 4A
whimpers, screams]
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH cry]
[clapping]
[TIAT gasping]
[LAKHESH whimpers]
Perfect ending.
That was so good!
[THEATRE PIG 4A squeals]
[TIAT sighs]
That was beautiful.
So mature!
Hope I fall in love one day!
Can I assume that wasn't
exactly your thing?
Nope. At least not
with the lizards.
There's been no word,
if you're still worrying.
Hard to believe it's already
been a couple of weeks.
Worrying is about all I can do.
Worrying and waiting.
At times like these, I find
it's best to stay busy,
don't you agree?
That being said,
mind doing me a favor?
What kind of favor?
[BAR MASTER 4A]
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but you're order is ready.
Sorry to interrupt, sorry!
Wow, that looks amazing.
Thank you so much, master!
I said I was sorry!
Please! Don't eat me.
Don't eat me!
[clattering]
[WILLEM] All right,
what did you do to him?
Nothing! What would I do?!
[WILLEM]
Not good.
Why they haven't called
in a professional
to fix this is beyond me.
Guess I can try
patching it, though.
Chtholly, will you get me
the hammer, please?
[WILLEM]
Chtholly?
Ithea?
Ren?
[WILLEM]
Chtholly?!
Ithea?!
Ren?!
Chtholly! Chtholly!
Chtholly!
[WILLEM panting]
[NYGGLATHO]
You must accept the truth.
[gasps]
[NYGGLATHO]
Have you forgotten, Willem?
We sent those three girls
off to battle for us.
[WILLEM gasping]
[NYGGLATHO]
You're not going to find them.
They're gone.
[WILLEM gasping]
We lost them, Willem.
They died.
They're all dead now.
[gasps]
[sighs]
These damn nightmares are
really starting to get to me.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling okay?
Uh? I, uh, aha!
Look over there,
we can finally see it!
Where, where is it?
Woo-hoo! Yes, I can see it!
Corna di Luce!
[CROWD chattering]
A hop, skip and a
jump away, my ass.
It took a full day
to get over here.
[inaudible]
Go figure. Apparently
even the disfeatured
can live normal
lives in this city.
[TIAT gasping]
It's such a beautiful place!
[NYGGLATHO]
Tiat had a dream.
It was of somewhere
she's never been before,
and of specific sights
that she's never seen.
She also even spoke with
someone she's never met.
It was that kind of dream.
Drinking milk is not gonna
make you taller immediately.
You know that, right?
Just 'cause it hasn't happened
doesn't mean it won't!
Tiat has been trying to drink as
much milk as she can every day!
I bet she'll just
shoot right up!
So is that unusual?
Sounds like a generic dream.
It's hardly generic.
Apparently, the girls can
tell there's a difference.
The moment they wake up,
they're aware that the dream
they had was a special one.
It's considered a harbinger.
All fairies who have the
harbinger dream are required
to get a checkup at Corna
di Luce's general hospital.
Huh?
[GOLEM 4A]
Have a good day.
[TIAT]
What?! Are you kidding me?!
That's the clock tower
from The Iguana Bride,
the movie that we just watched!
I'm in awe!
While we're here, are there
any sights you wanna see?
It's your first time out of
Island Sixty-Eight, yeah?
Uh? Thank you, but no.
I did not travel to this
island to have fun.
I'm here to follow my destiny
and become a great fairy
soldier like Chtholly.
Besides, what could I
possibly want to see.
I mean, really.
That's what I thought.
Don't worry, we have
plenty of time.
How about while we're on
the way to the hospital,
we stop at a few places
that look good?
Uh! Hm... Well.
All right. I guess it's fine.
If you're just dying
to sightsee that much,
then I don't mind
tagging along with you.
[WILLEM]
Me?
[TIAT]
Come on! We're wasting time.
Let's get going!
[TIAT humming]
[WILLEM]
Yeah, sure thing.
[TIAT]
Ahh!
Look! Can you even believe it?
Can I even believe it's a bench?
[TIAT] They used it in
When the Bell Rings Thrice !
In that exact spot,
the heroine wept
while holding her
former lover's tail!
[WILLEM] Is that another romance
movie with lizards?
You haven't heard of it before?!
While filming, the actress
playing the heroine
actually laid her eggs.
It was a really big deal!
[WILLEM]
Yeah. Sounds like a big deal.
[TIAT] Island Eleven's Corna Di
Luce happens to be the setting
of a bunch of different films.
I mean, of course it is.
It's overflowing with history.
A jewel in the sky!
It's practically a stew pot
of legend and adventure!
Did you just call it a stew pot?
[TIAT gasping]
That's the staircase
from the famous scene
in The Airship Thief ,
where the main couple got in
a fight and clawed each other!
I heard that the shed skin of
the lead actor fetched a fortune
at auction. I wonder
who bought it.
I'm so jealous!
Talk about lucky!
[WILLEM]
You sure do love lizards...
[screaming] In Each Scale
Is a Symbol of Love ,
the heroine and the soldier,
covered in scales,
smacked their tails right
below us in this river!
While filming, the director made
sure there was enough food
for every single person
working on set that day!
A million steel bottle flies,
can you even imagine that?
And did the cast and crew
actually eat that much food?
[WILLEM]
Right, very good question.
This is fascinating.
[GOLEM 4B]
Have a good day.
Whoa, this is the lickity café.
It was in Sweet Nest
and they did stuff
like those people over
there are doing.
I can't believe it's actually
happening in public like that,
in the middle of the day.
I don't really understand you,
but I still get the feeling kids
shouldn't be seeing that stuff.
Time's up, Tiat. Gotta go.
[TIAT gasping]
Random lizardness calls again.
[TIAT] The Great Sage statue
in Fulshter Memorial Plaza!
Oh, is it famous for something?
He founded this city
a long, long time ago,
but this is also
the most popular spot
for lovers' rendezvous.
Because of that, it appears in
several of my favorite movies.
[TIAT]
The fountain's good luck, too.
Legend says if a couple vows
their eternal love to each other
in front of it, they'll be happy
for at least five whole years.
If you ask me, that legend
is a serious disappointment.
[GOON 4A]
Destroy!
--Destroy! Destroy!
Please, I'm begging you.
That's all we've got!
Please stop, you don't
have to do this!
[OFFICER GOLEM 4A]
Cease and desist.
Uh. Let's go. C'mon!
[GOON 4B]
Yeah.
[CROWD gasping]
Move it!
[gasps]
[GOON 4A groans]
You'll pay for that!
[OFFICER GOLEM 4A]
You're under arrest.
[GOON 4A]
No! Damn it!
[WILLEM] Are you okay?
Oh, I'm good. Thank you.
Uh! Hey, put me down!
What are you thinking?!
I'm not a baby...!
[WILLEM]
Of course. I'm sorry.
[MAN 4A] Was it the
Annihilation Knights again?
[WOMAN 4A]
Don't you remember?
The stall's owner
supported the mayor.
What was that?
No matter where you go,
there are always people who have
too much time on their hands.
Whoa, we really have
to get moving.
Uh!
[WILLEM]
We don't want to be late, do we?
Punctuality and all that.
The sightseeing ends here!
Let's go, Willem.
I'm ready for this!
Wonder if she knows how
obvious it is that she's not.
[TIAT]
Come on, hurry up, Willem!
Coming!
[DOC 4A]
Tiat and Willem Kahmesh, yes?
NyNy told me you'd
be here today.
Who's NyNy?
Oh, you must mean Nygglatho.
I'm prepared to get the checkup
started if you are, Tiat.
All right, my dear.
You come with me.
[TIAT]
Uh... Oh, okay.
Hey, Tiat.
[TIAT]
Uh?
[WILLEM]
Looks like our airship back home
isn't until tomorrow evening.
[TIAT]
Hm?
We'll have some free time
once you're done.
We can probably take
an exploratory stroll.
If you want to, that is.
[gasps]
[laughing, humming]
[DOC 4A]
Oh, good. There you are.
Now, I've given health checks
to several of the girls
from the fairy warehouse before,
however, you are the
first caretaker
other than NyNy to make the
effort to accompany one here.
I think it's nice.
Anyway, Tiat will
be done shortly.
She's a sweet, responsible girl.
What exactly is
this checkup for?
Why do you ask,
did NyNy not inform you?
[WILLEM]
Not in detail, no.
[DOC 4A] Well, to start with,
not every fairy
has the capability
to wield a dug weapon.
The power is there, yes,
but it does not awaken
in all of the girls.
That must be where the
harbinger dream comes in.
It serves to awaken
the ability in them.
[DOC 4A]
Exactly.
What we do here is tune
their bodies to make sure
they grow up healthy and strong,
so they can fight one day
as proper dug wielders.
Our enemy is very powerful,
and our dug weapons precious.
Forcing swords onto children
when they're still immature
and weak would be pointless.
They're tuned, huh.
[DOC 4A] Tiat's growth is steady
and is as we expect of her age.
She has no major health
issues to speak of.
The only problems are
her digestive organs
are struggling to process all
the excess milk she drinks,
and a few of her teeth are
beginning to develop cavities.
I'll tell her to
back off the milk.
We have to accept that the
fairies are unnatural beings.
At times, a problem
may present itself
that severely affects
their bodies.
In the worst cases, they can
suffer mental disintegration.
Some lose their
minds completely.
But, in Tiat's case, if you
were worried about her,
there's really no reason to be.
That girl is firmly
in control of herself
as well as her potential.
To put it simply,
she's in great shape.
That's certainly
a relief to hear.
[door creaks]
Uh? Hey.
You all done with your checkup?
[TIAT]
Mm-hmm!
I'll stay the night,
and tuning will begin first
thing tomorrow morning!
We'll be finished with
everything by noon,
so you can come by and
pick her up around then.
[WILLEM]
Thank you.
Will you be okay?
Can you stay overnight
by yourself?
Ugh, of course I can stay!
I will be perfectly fine!
Um, will you be okay, though?
Where're you gonna stay tonight?
I'll be sleeping at the
Guardian Wings Military HQ.
Evidently, they have a resting
room for officers like me.
What does that mean?
I'm hoping it means I'm pretty
high up in the pecking order.
Oh, just wait.
I'll be all grown up tomorrow!
I've never been
this excited before!
Unfortunately, tuning
won't make you any taller.
Aw! What?! No, I was
counting on some height.
Try to hang in there anyway.
[DOC 4A]
We'll see you tomorrow.
Take care of our girl.
She will be all grown
up tomorrow.
Wow.
[WILLEM]
She doesn't really know.
How could she?
Becoming a soldier,
going off into battle so young.
[WILLEM] They're forced
to grow up too fast.
It's not fair.
[SOLDIER 4A] If you'll follow
me, Technical Officer Willem.
[WILLEM] Whoa, technical
officers actually do
rank high in the pecking order.
You're welcome to use this room
while you're staying here.
Goodnight, sir.
[WILLEM] Oh, one moment.
Sir?
You haven't by chance
heard anything about
the battle on Island Fifteen?
They were facing the timere?
[SOLDIER 4A] No, sir.
We've had no word, yet.
I see. Sorry to keep you.
You may go.
[SOLDIER 4A]
Yes, sir.
[door creaks]
[door slams]
[clock ticks]
So much for getting a
good night's sleep.
I think this bed was
actually too comfortable.
[WILLEM]
Might as well go for a walk.
I'm supposed to go
sightseeing with Tiat later.
I could go ahead
and plan the route.
[WILLEM] Thanks for nothing,
Corna di Luce.
See, I told you this was bad.
Let's patch it up for now
before it gets worse.
[SOLDIER 4B] And how do
you propose we do that?
Do you have a ladder that tall,
because I sure do not.
[SOLDIER 4C]
Right, you have a good point.
[SOLDIER 4B exhales]
Only one thing to do. We'll just
have to build a ladder
with whatever we can find.
[gasps]
[PHYRACORLYBIA gasps]
Sorry, are you all right?
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
I'm fine. Don't worry about it.
All right, then.
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
No, um, wait a second!
For what? I thought you said
not to worry about it, so...?
No, it's not that.
I wanted to say I was the one
to blame for running into you.
I'm keeping my blade sheathed.
Okay.
Very nice of you to say.
Hold on, your blade is what?
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
I wonder if you could help me.
I have an important request I
need to ask of Officer Limeskin.
Do you know if there's
any way I could see him?
Officer Limeskin?
I hate to tell you this, but
that giant lizard isn't here.
He's off fighting somewhere.
[gasps] Can you at least tell
me when he'll be coming back?
No, but I sincerely
wish I could.
They put up a damn magic field,
uh, they put up a barrier around
the battlefield for privacy.
We can't communicate.
--[SOLDIER 4D] You're sure?
--[SOLDIER 4E] Yes.
We have to send word.
[SOLDIER 4D]
This is confirmed?
You're sure it's about the
battle with the timere?
[gasps]
[PHYRACORLYBIA gasps]
Wait!
Tell me what happened!
[SOLDIER 4F]
I can't, it's classified.
The information I've been given
can only be circulated
on a regulated channel.
Pay attention,
and try that again.
I'm Officer Willem Kmetsh.
[SOLDIER 4F]
U-Uh! Forgive me, sir.
The dug weapons,
the fairy soldiers.
Both the dug weapons and the
wielders are under my care.
I should know-- I have the right
to know all the data pertaining
to them, and the news about
the battles they take part in.
This is an order.
I want you to tell me
everything you know!
What happened out there?!
Sir.
I just received an official
update from Fleet One.
The information is
regarding the results
of the battle on Island Fifteen.
The defense of the island.
The defense has failed.
[WILLEM gasps]
[SOLDIER 4F]
If you'll excuse me, sir.
What's wrong?
What did he say?
What is going on?
Are you all right, sir?
Hello? Hello?
Hello? Can you hear
what I'm saying, sir?
Oh, please answer me!
[CHTHOLLY]
The other day
you made sweets for the
little ones, remember?
That's what I want.
Can you make me
butter cake, maybe?
Sir, um, if you'd
only speak to me,
perhaps I could
help you somehow.
[SOLDIER 4G]
What?! Really?!
[SOLDIER 4H] We just received
it from General Command HQ.
[SOLDIER 4G]
How many casualties?
What about survivors?
[SOLDIER 4H] Fleet One of the
second Division has returned.
[SOLDIER 4G] We've received
an accurate casualty report!
[SOLDIER 4H]
Send medics, just in case!
[NEPHREN]
I think it would be best
if we send word as
soon as possible.
[ITHEA] Agreed. A certain
someone's heart
is probably jumping out
of his chest right now.
[CHTHOLLY]
But...
[gasps]
[LIMESKIN]
Given the circumstances,
I'll allow you to use the
communication crystals.
[ITHEA]
See?
We've even got the big bad
boss's permission.
[ITHEA]
Huh?
[CHTHOLLY] But when you use
a communication crystal,
the other person
can see us, too.
And I'm covered in mud.
I haven't even
taken a bath, yet.
Don't worry about that.
You're perfect as you are.
Uh?
Am not. Plus, I'm afraid
it would be kind of rude.
I'm just not mentally ready.
[gasping]
You're okay!
[screams]
[gasps]
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[CHTHOLLY]  Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait!
What is this?
What's going on?!
Ow, that's hurting.
I can't breathe.
Seriously, I can't breathe!
Did he pop up out of nowhere,
or was that just me?
I'm not sure, my eyes could
not keep up with him.
Perhaps he used
a secret, lost art?
This is why I said
I it would be best
to send word as
soon as possible.
Yes, you did, but admit it.
Like the rest of us,
you never expected to find
Willem this broken up.
No, you're right.
Are you even listening to me?!
Let me go!
I mean, this is bizarre,
especially considering
he usually likes to
play things cool.
Well, he's pretty cute
when he tries to play cool,
but that doesn't really
suit him, either.
Ha! Regardless,
I was expecting him
to be far less
emotional, you know?
This is just how Willem is,
hyper focused and hyper intense.
He needs to be looked after,
so he won't get hurt.
Yeah. That makes perfect sense.
I totally get where
you're coming from.
What do you think, Chtholly?
I think you should finish
your stupid conversation
and come help me!
[NEPHREN] Do you? Because
I feel like we should
let him embrace you
until he's satisfied.
No! Don't do it.
My spine will break,
I'll suffocate,
or I'll die of embarrassment
before that happens!
I dunno, if you can yell
like that, I seriously doubt
we need to worry too much
about you suffocating.
Please, don't worry.
We're all right here.
I promise we're not
going anywhere.
[whimpers]
Ren.
[NEPHREN]
Mmhmm.
[WILLEM]
Ithea.
Hey, what's up?
And then...
...Chtholly.
[CHTHOLLY]
Seriously, let me go already.
My heart can't take any more!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[gasps]
Things are gettin' a lil' messy.
[grunts]
[smack]
[WILLEM] Next Episode:
from dawn till dusk.