H'yah!
It's so cold.
Where'd this come from?
Chtholly? Are you up yet?
Ugh, I'm bored. I'm bored. I'm bored.
I'm so bored, bored, bored, bored, bored!
Nopht, stop. Please be quiet.
Come on, I know you've gotta be bored, too, Rhan.
What is that? Ancient book?
Yes, one of yesterday's finds.
Are you telling me you can read emnetwiht writing?
I can connect the dots between the words.
After that, it's just an educated guess.
Ah. Well?
What are the emnetwihts saying?
The human race...
should have... never come into being.
The visitors were who created
them, and the cost was great.
The gods failed. Blame the gods.
They failed us. It was their biggest mistake.
That's crazy.
Remember, this isn't 100%. It's a best guess.
Beasts by humans.
Truth unleash.
Oh, this might be the other way around.
Humans unleash the beasts,
and fill the world with, with the ashen truth.
Oh wow!
Yes, I know. Now, get off me.
Sounds to me like your book is talking
about the beasts destroying the surface.
Like a prophecy. Something wild like that.
It's not.
This seems to be a fairy tale or a textbook of sorts.
I think it's more likely humans created
the beasts in accordance with this idea.
At least, that would be the natural
assumption. Yeah, it makes sense.
Uh?
However, it almost seems like...
Who's there?
Hey, I'm looking for the waiting
room for the fleet escort. Is this it?
I'm a salvager with your fellow passengers,
the Orlandry Merchant Guild.
Everybody calls me Grick, 'cause it's my name.
Chtholly!
I'm so happy you're not a ghost!
Oh, Tiat...
Sorry, she hasn't fully recovered from everything yet.
Poor thing was out of sorts
the entire time you were broken.
So, please be patient with her outburst.
I was.
I don't know why.
For some reason, I just felt so down.
I see. I also see that you've grown taller.
Hello, Chtholly!
You're all better now, right?
Well, good morning.
You feelin' okay?
Uh. Uh-huh.
Good morning.
Are you going on a trip?
Is that why you're wearing your hat?
Oh, no.
My hair refused to cooperate
today, so I'm trying to hide it.
Anyway, tell me how practice was this morning!
Piece of cake!
Oh, I made me hungry.
That's enough, girls.
Breakfast will be ready when you're ready.
Meaning after you've all washed up.
Yes, ma'am!
All right, let's make our escape now.
Not eating breakfast with us?
Just in case,
I want her to get checked out as soon as possible.
Of course.
Um, bye.
So you're the survey unit's adviser, then?
That's me.
I figured I should at least come greet
those who hold my life in their hands!
Can't hurt to be nice to the ones
in charge of protecting my crew!
That's a weird thing to say.
We look like we're beast fighters?
You can't honestly believe the two of us can protect you.
Frankly, no, not at all. It's
still hard for me to accept.
Really, it seems as if it's some kind of stupid joke.
But the thing is,
you're here and you've got dug weapons with you.
Matches everything I've heard
about your kind too perfectly.
Whadda they call you again?
Leprechauns?
That's right.
You sure do know a whole lot.
I have a couple of friends who
keep me pretty well informed.
Now. Here, I brought you a token of friendship!
You haven't been home in more than a month.
I bet you miss good food.
Picked these up on Island Thirty-One on my way here.
Hope you like meat pies!
You can't possibly be serious!
I'll have you know our favor is not so easily bought.
We'll gladly take them.
Rhan, how can you say that?
As it turns out, at the moment we
have nothing in particular to do.
We could talk to him for a bit.
I think there's no harm in that.
Whatever.
It's fine with me if it's fine with you!
Now, then.
"Grick," was it?
That's right.
Have you been a salvager very long?
Yeah, I suppose you could say that.
Really?
Have you ever run into a beast?
Huh? Why would you ask that question, you actually
think you can learn something about those things from me?
Yes.
I want to know more. To start with, what are they?
Where and how were the beasts even born?
Why did they wipe out the emnetwihts on the surface?
You seem to care an awful lot about them.
Yes, while the beasts may threaten your very existence,
they are the reason for ours.
Isn't it natural to be curious about one's origin?
I would learn a lot more if I could
just bite off a little piece of your flesh.
Please don't.
Nygglatho.
Is there anything wrong?
Like with my body, I mean.
Hm. Is there something wrong?
Don't worry, I wouldn't call it "wrong."
Thanks for shopping with me.
It was nice.
I appreciate you carrying the stuff back, too.
I also had an errand to run, so don't even mention it.
From what I understand,
you've been working at that bakery for quite a while.
How did that happen?
The military brass did not like the idea at all,
but Nygglatho helped convince them to let me do it.
And what do you think, Officer Willem?
How do you feel about us weapons working for money?
Is there something wrong with
wanting to be like everyone else?
I feel like grown-ups are supposed to ensure
that kids can do whatever they want within reason.
As long as it's not dangerous
or plain wrong, it's okay with me.
Thank you!
Oh, I love you so much, Officer Willem!
I've never had a father before,
but you seem like what a father should be.
That's sweet to say.
I actually already consider you
girls to be my kids, more or less.
You really do?
Hold on, if you're our father, then
what person would that make our mother?
Maybe Nygglatho?
Doesn't seem fair to Chtholly.
All right, time to get going.
I have to start the cooking, now.
I gave you the silver test,
and it came up negative.
It did? Wow, okay.
What does that mean?
Silver powder has a natural reaction to irregular death.
To put it simply, it's a drug we
use to detect the presence of spirits.
And since leprechauns are a type of spirit,
I was expecting your blood to turn black immediately
after I mixed it together with the silver testing agent.
But there was no reaction at all.
I don't know the reason, but right now,
your body is not scientifically a leprechaun's.
Wait! What are you talking about?
Then, what's happened to my body?!
I have no idea.
It's just the only conclusion that I can make, well,
based on the findings.
Is that... Is that why my hair is changing?
There's the possibility it could
be a side effect of your coma.
Nygglatho, what's going to happen to me?
You honestly don't feel anything
wrong with your body?
No, I don't.
I feel perfectly normal.
Well, then. I guess try not to worry about it for now.
Give me time to do a little
more research. I'll figure it out.
And don't get any ideas about dyeing your hair.
I doubt that it's gonna bother Willem.
Why would you say that?!
Uh?
Until we get all of this cleared up,
I want you to be sure and stay away from your dug weapon.
There's just no telling what might happen.
All right. I can do that.
Although, what am I gonna do if I can't wield a sword?
I dunno.
Maybe you can work on getting married instead?
I'm being serious here.
Surely, you realize Willem's
contract will eventually expire.
Of course, we both know how he is.
I'm certain he would stay if we all asked him.
Then, can't we just do that?
Of course not! Asking is way too easy.
Instead, we'll aggressively
remind him that this is his home.
Then, no one will have to ask him at all!
And obviously, the best way to make him feel like
this is his home is for him to have a wife and family.
What? Is that how this stuff really works?
That is how this stuff works.
Honestly, I was considering volunteering
myself for the job in question, but I thought...
Please don't!
If you did, then...
then I wouldn't stand a chance.
I suppose it's time for you to start fishing.
You better work some magic and hook that man fast.
Don't procrastinate, either.
Otherwise, me or some other
girl will get him before you do.
Time to dig in!
Whoa! It's heaven.
You're a little too good at this stuff, T.O.
What does that mean?
You knew she wouldn't eat it
if you only baked some for her,
so you found a way to make
sure she had her cake and ate it.
I gotta say, I'm impressed you baked enough for all of us!
Pretty good, if I do say so myself.
Hey, Ren. Where is she?
Um, probably her room.
Why, did something happen?
No, she just prefers not to eat
sweets in front of anyone else.
Mm-hm. She likes to think she's fancy.
But, it's not as if it bothers her that much.
You should totally take some to her room yourself
and spend some sugary-sweet "quality" time together.
Heh.
Don't make it sound inappropriate.
It's just, I dunno.
The other girls look up to me, so I
don't want to look childish in front of them.
And um, from what I've been told,
when I eat stuff like that...
...let's just say that I could ruin my own reputation.
With sweets, I kinda go crazy.
What is that look for?
You're making a really big deal
out of something that's ridiculous,
which sorta proves that you're still a kid.
Excuse me?!
Shall I also get you some tea?
Well, my lady?
Heh.
It smells so delicious.
It is.
Looks delicious.
Yes, that's because it is.
You sure?
Like, it's okay for me to eat this in front of you?
Do you even need to ask?
Who do you think I baked it for, silly?
I kept my promise.
I did it.
Must've been rough.
Yes.
Yes!
It was, it was so hard.
I know I said this yesterday,
but welcome home, Chtholly.
I'm home.
I made it back.
I finally got to say it.
And I finally got to hear it.
Does it look weird?
The red hair?
It's a very pretty color, and it looks great.
Oh, good. Thank you.
All right. I'm fine now.
You sure about that?
You're not feeling sick or anything?
I'll be mad at you if you push yourself.
I'm fine!
And I have cooking, laundry, and lots
of other responsibilities to focus on.
There's no reason to get upset.
I know.
Just wait. I hope that you're ready!
That's what I said!
Ladies! Did you forget something?
Like wiping your shoes off before coming inside?!
Huh? Sorry, Chtholly.
If I'm really freed from being a fairy soldier...
If I'm really allowed to pursue my dreams,
the same dreams as most normal people, then...
I want to live, standing side by side with him.
I want to see the same things, walk down the same path,
eat the same food, and go to the same places he goes.
I want to spend my whole life that way, with him.
Getting better at homey stuff is all well and good,
but I mean like...?
It's only for Willem?
Look at who's making another spicy meat dish!
And seems to me this one's tailored
to a certain someone's taste buds, too.
Oh, shut up and get out of here! Only the
person cooking is allowed in the kitchen anyway!
It's a very pretty color, and it looks great.
Ooh-hoo.
What? You were eavesdropping!
Ha, ha! Amazing how girls in love are so full of life!
What?!
Although, I don't know about hogging the whole kitchen.
I mean, that sure is a lot of work
just to get to one guy's stomach.
How is said fairy soldier?
It's been around five days since she
woke up, and so far, she seems fine.
Does she?
Good, that's wonderful to hear.
Uh, so...
What's with the getup?
They're civilian clothes.
I happen to be under suspension
for leading a losing battle.
I can't wear a uniform right now.
Hopefully, this is only temporary.
Uh-huh. So uh,
why are we making off-duty lizards come all this way?
What's this conversation about?
To discuss Chtholly's immediate future, right?
Did I not mention that to you earlier?
I thought we three needed to talk about it.
Hm?
Those girls are technically weapons.
It's not like they can retire.
And, although Chtholly is not a leprechaun at the moment,
she's still considered a fairy soldier on paper.
Which means she can't turn down an order to sortie, huh.
So then what about on your end?
You're first officer, could you adjust the sortie lineup?
I could if I was in charge, but there's a chance
the order might come from higher up in the command.
Hold on.
You know the Great Sage?
Doesn't he have military influence?
--Huh? --What?
Yes, I know him.
He's the military's top advisor,
everyone knows the Great Sage.
Then make sure he receives
a report that goes like this:
"In order to research leprechaun physiology,
Technical Officer Kmetsch has chosen soldier
Chtholly Nota Seniorious to be a test subject."
What is that about?
Just call it a hunch.
If I ask to be given responsibility for her,
I bet he'll agree to it.
Mostly because he'll assume that'll make me owe him one.
So what kind of relationship do you
imagine you have with the Great Sage?
Don't worry about that,
worry about how we're going to replace Chtholly.
Ithea and Ren can't handle it,
not if they're by themselves.
Oh.
Right, well, about that. There's, uh...
Hm?
I heard from the guild that beasts
attacked the surface survey team.
Apparently, the Saxifraga was sunk.
Saxi...
It sunk? What of the warriors that were aboard?
Both were a bit worn out, however, apparently unhurt.
Hang on a second, you guys.
"Survey team"? "Both"?
Oh, yeah.
I keep forgetting that you only
arrived here like a month ago.
Do you actually know how many
battle-ready fairies we currently have?
Aside from Chtholly, three.
That's with Tiat, who hasn't been paired with a sword.
No, we have five girls ready.
There's Ithea, and Nephren, Tiat, I guess.
We also have Nopht and Rhantolk.
Well, where are those girls right now?
You could try putting two and two together?
No way...
Yes way.
I think that's correct, but how can we really know...
What is that?
It's a Beast!
You idiot!
That thing reacts to sound and motion.
Just be still and keep quiet.
Come on. What the hell is goin' on over there?
Huh?
Wow, that is not a good sign.
I expected a beast to put up a better fight.
Completely insane.
Are you talking about the beast?
Or perhaps...?
Next Episode: slight light, slight hope.