[clock ticking]
[clock chimes]
[WILLEM grunts]
[WILLEM sighs]
This place is a disaster.
It's ridiculous...
I doubt this room's
ever been cleaned up.
Maybe no one uses it?
[door creaks]
[WILLEM]
Or maybe they do.
What are you up to, Nephren?
[slurping]
[BOTH sigh]
It's Ren.
You can just call me Ren.
[WILLEM] Well, thanks
for the coffee, Ren.
May I ask you what you're
doing here so late?
I've been looking for your
sortie records, actually.
Those are in the junk room?
Need some help?
Sure, if you don't mind.
After that, I want to find
the files on timeres.
I need to know sortie
frequency and timing,
any strength differentials,
overall losses,
that sort of thing. The more
I can learn, the better.
[NEPHREN] Roger. You're asking
a lot, but I'll do it.
[WILLEM] Great. Think we can
get it done by morning?
[NEPHREN]
Mm.
[bell tolls]
[CHTHOLLY grunting]
[CHTHOLLY] If I were
gonna die in five days,
like hypothetically,
do you think you'd be
a little nicer to me?
A kiss?
What if I asked to kiss you?
Just once.
That was a dream.
There's no way I could've
said that to him!
[gasps]
[CHTHOLLY screams]
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[screams]
[CHTHOLLY] What have I done?
What have I done?
You all right in here, Chtholly?
I'm fine!
Good. You sound fine.
I bet that's a relief.
Usually after a battle, you
seem to be in a lot of pain.
Well, that's because...
Wait, I don't feel as bad today.
Of course not!
You've got heart and spirit!
Wait, last night.
That's what he was doing.
[CHTHOLLY screams]
[CHTHOLLY] Girls, um, do you
know where he is?
Y'mean do we know where
Officer Willem is?
Uh, let's see.
He's sleeping with Nephren!
[LAKHESH whines]
[yawning]
Such a savage fairy weapon.
[CHTHOLLY growls]
[WILLEM]
Chtholly. Good morning.
Yes, good morning.
So, you spent the
whole night together.
And what were you doing?
Nothing important.
Trying to find a way for you to
avoid opening the Fairy Gate.
We just didn't want you
to die, that's all.
You don't understand, do you?
We have to be the ones to fight
because it's the only
way to take them out.
[WILLEM]
Are you positive about that?
Huh?
I'm positive we don't
have a choice!
And we certainly don't
need your pity!
[WILLEM] It's good to see
you're feeling better.
[CHTHOLLY]
Wait, what?
Come with me, and get a
dose of morning exercise.
[WILLEM grunts]
[WILLEM]
Chtholly.
Do you think you're ready
to give up your life
in order to secure a future
for the rest of these kids?
What are you asking me that for?
Think you're any good?
I'm just curious.
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
The leprechauns are the only
creatures that can wield
dug weapons. Put that down!
Don't be so sure.
There's a decent chance I can
wield one better than you.
[CHTHOLLY]
Really...?
Challenge accepted.
I hope you don't regret this.
But you will!
Hold on, what just happened?
Wow, is that all you've got?
[CHTHOLLY grunting]
You?!
Yeah?
How dare you?!
[CHTHOLLY grunting]
What's going on?!
How'd you do that?
Listen to me.
These carillons,
that is to say dug weapons,
they're powerful swords, yes,
but they do not gain potency
from the wielder's
output of venenum.
What? You're not serious.
Oh, but I am.
These weapons use
the enemy's own force
against them as soon
as contact is made.
The stronger the opponent,
the more lethal the sword.
[gasps]
[WILLEM]
Think about it!
There has to be a better way
to battle these beasts
than what you've been
doing, hasn't there?
[CHTHOLLY grunts]
A way with less sacrifice, with
less self-destruction nonsense.
[CHTHOLLY]
How dare you?
What could you possibly
understand about us?
[WILLEM] You fight without
knowing the basics,
which means you can only swing
your sword with brute force.
It seems you're the one
who doesn't understand.
[screams] What's your problem?!
Who do you think you are,
showing up out of nowhere
and acting as if you
have all the answers?!
I'm the man who knows
your fighting style
is nowhere near good
enough to win.
[CHTHOLLY yells]
[CHTHOLLY]
I won't accept this!
I can't accept it!
Everything we've done
has not been a mistake!
[CHTHOLLY yells]
Will you, listen to me?!
[CHTHOLLY]
No!
[WILLEM] I can explain to
you how the dug weapons
are actually meant to work!
[CHTHOLLY]
He's wrong!
[WILLEM] I want you to learn
the proper way to fight,
and to wield Seniorious!
[CHTHOLLY]
He's lying!
[WILLEM]
You don't have to die.
None of you have to die.
[CHTHOLLY]
But, we do...
[WILLEM]
Your movements are sharp.
I like your instincts, too.
And your venenum flow
is pretty special.
This is a relief.
You're plenty strong.
What's more, you will be
able to get stronger.
That being said...
[splash]
Come back alive or else I'll,
I dunno, something...
[CHTHOLLY]
Uh?
[gasps]
[CHTHOLLY]
What's wrong with him?
[NYGGLATHO]
Just to confirm.
In three days at exactly
eight o'clock,
we will dispatch three
of our wielders,
along with their individual
dug weapons,
from the port at
Island Sixty-Eight.
The fairy that wields Seniorious
will be in attendance
with the understanding that...
[NYGGLATHO]
That during this operation,
it will be her responsibility
to open the Fairy Gate.
Yes, we are confirmed.
[NYGGLATHO sighs] Why must it
always be one of our girls
to make the sacrifice?
They die before ever
getting the chance
to experience what life
truly has to offer.
[NYGGLATHO sobs]
I hate this! I hate it!
Why does it have
to be this way?!
Sorry to be a bother.
[NYGGLATHO] You should be.
Why didn't you knock?
It's an emergency.
A bad one.
Willem's going to die!
[EBONCANDLE]
You managed to defeat me?
Your strength is impressive,
even for a human.
However, you must know
all those spells you cast
will return to torment
you as curses.
[EBONCANDLE] I shall now slumber
for a century.
Sadly, I've not been
blessed with enough time
to watch you expire.
[WILLEM]
Go, then, demon.
Enjoy your sleep.
Let me die in peace.
[EBONCANDLE laughs]
As you wish, human brave.
Farewell.
[WILLEM] I've always known I
would be fated to this end.
May it not be in vain.
Lillia, I'm sorry.
Souwong, please forgive me.
[WILLEM]
I leave the rest to you, now.
Almaria, I truly am sorry.
A dream.
Yes, and a nightmare
by the looks of it.
What happened to you?
Your bones are all broken,
and your organs are
barely functional.
In fact, your muscles
are so frail,
I could have easily
bitten them off.
Not as satisfying as
you'd hoped?
This isn't a joke,
I'm seriously worried!
I don't know what happened, but
how can you live in this state?
I call them my battle scars.
[NYGGLATHO]
From before we ever met?
Yes. It wasn't very
easy being me.
[sighs] Try to get some rest.
And no getting out
of bed, mister.
[WILLEM grunts]
Now this story happened
a long time ago.
In those days,
I was on the surface
helping a group of salvagers
find anything to sell.
While exploring one day,
we came across
what appeared to be a
frozen underground lake.
[NYGGLATHO] That's where we
found him, frozen in ice.
[NYGGLATHO] Our investigation
revealed that he'd been placed
under a petrification curse.
We decided it would be best
to take him back to
the sky islands with us.
[WILLEM groaning]
[NYGGLATHO] When he woke up,
he was in a panic.
It didn't help that we couldn't
communicate with each other.
But, thankfully, he was
wearing a babel talisman.
That's what eventually solved
our communication dilemma.
Without it, we may never have
learned who he really was.
The human race had alienated
all the other races
and were forced to fight alone.
They had been wiped out, along
with the rest of surface life.
But as luck would have it,
the wretched race we call
emnetwihts had one survivor.
Willem Kmetsch.
[NYGGLATHO] I know how
this must make you feel.
I just don't want it
to make you fear him.
I don't want you
to hate him, either.
Girls, please, y--
[GIRLS yelling, laughing]
Wait for me!
Huh?
Ooh Ooh! Willem!
What's this I hear about you
being wiped out?
[TIAT]
This is fascinating, emnetwihts
aren't really all that
different from us.
Very intriguing.
Tell me all about your people,
and leave nothing out!
Willem, I...
Well, don't take this
the wrong way.
But, you should cheer up!
Already cheer.
I'm so hungry.
[GIRLS gasp]
[GIRLS whimper]
[GIRLS scream]
Please, wait!
What am I gonna do
with them? Silly girls.
[ITHEA] Ah! Well, that sure
made things quieter.
And you better keep it down,
too. I wasn't kidding.
I am hungry.
[ITHEA laughs]
Oh, no, don't you worry.
All I wanted is to ask that
half-dead man who's apparently
the last living
emnetwiht a question.
Go ahead. What is it?
Well, I'm wondering why
a great emnetwiht,
why you would go so far for us.
You risked your life for
basically no reason.
I mean...
That's totally disgusting.
Right. I guess so?
Isn't it only natural to wanna
be nice to cute kids, though?
Especially if they're girls?
Cute is relative, and
we're all girls here,
gender should have
nothing to do with
whether or not you're kind.
I didn't mean to offend,
it's my opinion.
I just think girls are cuter.
It reflects the way
they want to be loved.
They adorably wish to be adored.
Boys are cute too,
just in a smellier way.
And adorable applies to us?
Come on, as a race,
you're generally all born
in this form, right?
Can't be this cute for nothing.
So you're telling me
everyone in my race
is really desperate
for attention?
How funny, this coming
from someone
who's practically obsessed
with little girls.
Oh! Of course! I get it!
No, I don't think you do!
[NYGGLATHO, ITHEA laugh]
[NYGGLATHO]
You walked right into that one!
[NEPHREN]
Chtholly...?
[CHTHOLLY]
There's just no way.
I refuse to believe he's right.
It seems you're the one
who doesn't understand.
I'm the man who knows
your fighting style
is nowhere near good
enough to win.
[GIRL 3A]
It's all yours, now.
All right. I'm off!
[CHTHOLLY laughs]
[CHTHOLLY]
I was so scared.
Terrified.
[CHTHOLLY] It took what
seemed like an eternity
to resign myself to my fate.
[CHTHOLLY cries]
[CHTHOLLY]
I don't want to go back.
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
I'm sorry to arrive
without notice.
It's nothing.
Proud warriors will always have
a safe place here with us,
should they need to
escape their winds.
That's good to know.
Thank you, Officer Limeskin.
Bitter...
Do you want to talk about it?
I don't think so.
Besides, it's probably
too late to say
I'm afraid of dying, isn't it?
[CHTHOLLY] Technical Officer
Willem showed me a new
fighting style, different from
anything I've ever seen.
And I can't...
I can't accept what he says!
Because that would mean that the
older fairies all died in vain!
I can't...
It struck fear in you?
Seems so...
I see! Of course.
Don't be concerned,
that man is simply
trying to fight the wind
that blows within you.
The wind?
I've heard some warriors refer
to their wind as their resolve.
But I suppose resignation is an
acceptable equivalent, too.
Do you think my doubts mean
I lack a warrior's resolve?
I don't.
Resignation does
not have to mean
you lack anything, Chtholly.
No matter the word, you've
cast aside what others
consider precious in order
to achieve a goal.
You're a warrior,
and all warriors have
wind in their hearts.
On their aimless path, it
gives them some direction.
Once the battle ends,
their souls remain pure
and are able to find
the rest they so deserve.
Thanks, Officer.
But, I um...
I didn't understand any of that.
Is that so?
Can I...
I'd like to make a confession,
even if it gets me in trouble.
The thing is...
Well, I've never actually
wanted to be a warrior.
[LIMESKIN chuckles]
You're looking good, Seniorious.
Way to hang in there.
[WILLEM] Ooh. The runaway
girl hath returned.
I just went out for a stroll.
What are you doing?
[WILLEM] A little maintenance
on your partner.
Did it cross your mind
to ask the wielder
for permission first?
[CHTHOLLY]
A beautiful performance.
[WILLEM]
Heh. Performance, huh?
I've never seen these lights.
What are they?
These are shining talismans.
It's how carillons are made.
Various shining talismans
join together
and form the shape of a sword.
Huh.
Then all these lights,
they're from wishes people
have made, aren't they?
The talisman that you
flicked just then?
It was created to help you
avoid burning your tongue
on a hot beverage.
Uh?
The one next to it let's you
know which way is north,
even if you're in a place that
you've never been before.
And the lights there
directly above it
can prevent nightmares
when you have a cold.
One can help you
imitate cat meows--
This is Seniorious. It's a
legendary weapon, right?
Apparently, when you connect
different talismans using magic,
it causes a complex reaction
that gives them entirely new
and captivating
effects like this.
[CHTHOLLY]
I guess I thought
since it's a
legendary holy sword
that it would have a more
extraordinary origin.
[WILLEM]
Sorry to disappoint.
[CHTHOLLY] So, I spoke with
First-Grade Officer Limeskin.
He said he would
leave it up to me,
that I can make my own decision.
I don't have to open the Fairy
Gate if I don't want to.
He'd stake the
island's fate on it.
He trusts my potential
as well as resolve.
That's wonderful.
So I can grow stronger,
and you really believe that?
I don't just believe it.
I can make it happen.
[gasps]
All right, I'll take you
up on it, but first...
Yes, what?
You might wanna know,
I actually don't
want to be strong!
No, that's not how it should go.
You're supposed to
notice my affection
and accept my offer
while crying.
Heh! Sorry, but I'm being
as accepting as I can.
Because you can't take a hint.
Stupid.
Fine then, if you manage
to come back alive.
I'll grant you one wish,
anything you want.
[gasps]
Wait, you can't ask me to marry
you or that kind of crap.
But you said anything!
You have to pick something
that's grounded in reality.
[CHTHOLLY grumbles]
[gasps] Sweets.
Uh?
[CHTHOLLY] The other day you
made sweets for the little ones,
remember? That's what I want.
Can you make butter cake, maybe?
[WILLEM gasping]
[ALMARIA] I'll feed you
so much of that cake,
you're bound to get heartburn.
A girl I used to know,
an older fairy,
whenever she returned from a
battle she'd devour butter cake
like her life genuinely
depended on it.
But they don't offer it on the
menu in the mess hall anymore.
I've never been able
to imitate her.
That's what I want.
Please.
Of all the bizarre things...
Willem?
Don't worry. I'm fine.
[WILLEM]
And you're on.
I'll feed you enough
to give you heartburn.
[WILLEM]
It's a deal.
Now, you just have
to come back alive.
[CHTHOLLY]
You got it.
[GRICK]
What's goin' on?
You didn't want to meet
me all the way here
for lunch for no reason.
I tuned their swords
as much as I could,
and I taught them
everything I know.
They should be ready.
Well, then, why aren't you
out there seeing them off?
I don't know why, but
it's not like it's going to
improve their
chances of victory.
[GRICK]
Hey, You never know.
A heart full of faith could make
way for a mysterious power!
[WILLEM]
No, it won't.
We all wish it could,
but it won't.
[GRICK] My friend,
you are far too cynical.
[WILLEM laughs]
[CHTHOLLY] All right.
It looks like we're off!
[WILLEM]
Oh, yeah.
Do you know any shops that
sell butter and flour?
Not too pricey.
[WILLEM]
Next Episode: dice in pot.