Just try not to over think it, okay?
The truth of the matter is, it's us. We're
the special weapons. You get to care for us.
So, what's after breakfast?
Play?
We're the special weapons.
--Stop it that's mine! --No, it's not it's mine!
Go find somewhere to sit so you can eat.
Hey! No running!
Good morning, ladies.
Your attention, please.
These girls, they're the special weapons.
Allow me to introduce you.
This gentleman is Second-Grade Technical Officer
Willem, and he will be living with us from now on.
I'm very pleased to meet you all.
Uh.
You three are awake early!
You up for a duel?
No, thanks.
Should be easier, now.
Lakhesh's gonna get eaten!
Or kidnapped for ransom!
I'm not gonna get kidnapped.
I'm not, right?
Please put me down.
This way!
Hi.
Uh.
Don't take it personally.
The children here aren't used to having adult men around,
so they don't know how to interact with one.
Yes, I understand that.
I just wish I knew a way to keep from terrifying them.
Honestly, it's depressing.
Well, of course it would be!
So, Officer Willem, you like little girls, do ya?
I like kids, yes.
Wow. Then, you admit it.
Now, I'm dying to know which one is your type!
There's me, the lovably boisterous Ithea.
Capricious lil' Nephren here.
Although, if I were to make a recommendation,
I'd say go with fresh-faced and moody.
Chtholly. We've met.
Hold on, when did that happen?
Moving a bit fast, aren't ya?
You gotta tell me everything!
Cut it out, Ithea!
Okay, it's been cut.
I find you three and all the little ones very cute.
What? You're lumping me in with children?
You're not much older than them.
That's not true! I'll have
you know I'm 15 years old!
And now I wanna know if that
falls within the officer's range.
Ithea, shut up!
Back to the point, I wish I could think of a
good way to get the little ones to open up to me.
Even when you're agonizing like that,
you... look... delicious.
Nygglatho! What's that?
You're supposed to be the adult.
You can't just go around licking people!
Great plan! I bet something
tasty will win 'em over real fast!
Is that what she meant?!
Of course!
Uh?
That's perfect!
So you can cook, huh?
I guess just a bit.
A man who can help around the
house is definitely a keeper!
Valid.
Where'd you pick up that so-called wisdom?
Looks good.
Here, tell me what you think.
I'll pass, thanks, though.
Really?
All right.
It's yummy.
What do you think? Ready to dig in, girls?
Yeah!
This is the bestest, ever!
You've certainly changed, haven't you?
Not that I didn't love it, but before, you were always
what I considered one of those "aloof degenerate" types.
--Is something wrong? --Yeah.
I forgot who I was for just a moment there.
Won't happen again.
It won't?
Oh my.
Seconds, please!
Whoa!
What was that about forgetting who you were?
I think it's safe to say you
got them to open up to you.
I did. Kids are funny. They're just great.
Hearts on their sleeves.
Very true.
Oh, by the way.
You didn't have to help me clean up, but thank you.
You're welcome.
It's a good distraction.
Uh. What do you mean? Do you need a distraction?
No, not really.
I think we're finally done!
Yay! Cleanup complete!
Goodnight, then.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay. Goodnight.
Here we go!
All right, it's my turn, now!
No, I'm throwing it!
Girls, that's enough, stop fighting.
Calm down. Don't be weird.
Can't stop thinking about him?
Wow, interesting reaction.
Why are you acting like that?!
Acting like what?
I just think it's funny how
everyone's taken to Willem so fast.
I mean, it's practically like he's
already been here for years, ya know?
Yes, I do.
I like your new hat.
It must mean a lot considering you
keep it safely hidden in your closet.
Oh. Yeah, she's
obsessed with it.
Uh! No, it doesn't mean anything to me.
I just prefer to keep it out of the way
because you don't need a hat like that very often.
Yeah, right.
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean what do I mean?
Hey, Ren, you interested in him, too?
Not really.
Though I do find him... curious, I suppose.
Meaning, you're interested in him.
Chtholly.
How many days are left as of now?
Around ten.
I don't know if that's enough time for a romance, but,
you might as well give it a shot, you know?
Will you please leave it alone?
Don't be so timid.
In this day and age, lots of
fairies never even hit adolescence.
You did that and fell in love,
which basically means you won life.
It isn't like that.
I see. I'll search the study for any
books that might help in this endeavor.
Oh, not you, too.
Ugh! Don't bother!
Can we focus and get dressed already?
Is that not what we're doing?
Never saw it comin'. Hi-yah!
Collon, what are you thinking?
Tiat's on your team!
Whatever works.
I got it!
Stop rolling, ball!
Almita!
Hey!
Almita! Are you all right?
Yeah. I think so.
Ouchie.
I fell down hard!
Stay still. You're bleeding.
I'm fine, don't worry.
Almita! Get the dumb ball!
It's right over there!
Hurry up!
You girls are...
You appear to have something you'd like to share with me.
I didn't realize it until earlier today.
These children.
They're not at all concerned about their lives.
They're not.
I know it can be unnerving how indifferent they are.
It's not normal.
Who and what are these girls?
I get why you ask, but, to be
honest, I'd rather not answer.
Are you sure you wanna know the truth?
Once you know, your attitude towards them will
change, and you won't be able to help yourself.
I just...
I don't want that change in you to hurt their feelings.
The past few days, you've
acted like a very nice young man.
While, at first, I found that side of you a little creepy,
now, I'm thankful for how kind and generous you've been.
If it's at all possible, I'd like
things to stay this way for a while longer.
I want to know.
I assume you're already aware of the 17 beasts?
Yes, they were created 500 years ago by foolish humans.
I mean, emnetwihts.
Awfully self-deprecating, aren't we?
Of course, not long after their creation, the beasts wiped
out all life on the surface, including the emnetwihts.
That wasn't enough for the beasts, though.
Our skies are in constant jeopardy of their next attack.
Which begs the question,
how do we defend ourselves against them?
The answer lies beyond this door.
Are those... carillons?
We call them "dug weapons" now.
These instruments are our only
means of fighting the 17 beasts.
Insania.
Ignareo.
Percival.
As I recall,
Carillons were special.
So special, in fact, that only chosen
emnetwiht braves could wield them.
Correct.
So, with the emnetwihts gone now,
how are they still working?
Who's using them to fight?
Well, surely, you already know.
But how...?
The girls are leprechauns.
Fairies who have imitated emnetwihts since ancient times.
That means they have the ability to use emnetwiht weapons.
The difference?
Their bodies were created to be expended in battle.
ecause of that, they have no fear of death.
You wanted to know what they were.
You have your answer.
I hope you can handle it.
I'll be fine.
So those girls are your partners, now?
Huh.
Pannibal, you're going too fast!
Wait!
Hello, Nephren. All alone?
Where are Chtholly and Ithea?
They both went out.
They both went out,
and did not return until several days later.
Venenum output is inversely proportional
to a spell caster's life force.
The more they want to live, the lower the output.
For those who care nothing about their
lives, the output rises drastically.
Such power cannot be contained and quickly
grows out of control causing a massive explosion.
Both spell caster and enemy will be obliterated,
leaving the dug weapon as the lone survivor of the blast.
Yes.
I'm sure those girls make excellent weapons.
If it isn't Officer Willem. Long time no see!
Hey, are you two all right?
What?! Yeah, sure, I'm fine!
And she's...
Well, she's napping 'cause she's worn out.
That's a relief.
Fancy running into you here, though.
Out on a walk?
Nygglatho told me you were
back, so I'm here to pick you up.
Wait, does that
mean that you, um...
Knew that you were away fighting?
Seventeen beasts and all that.
I can't believe it!
Talk about embarrassing.
You must be who I'm looking for.
Technical Officer Willem, that correct?
Yes.
And who exactly are you?
I'm here to give you their weapons.
Return them to the vault immediately.
These are Seniorious and Valgulious, right?
Wow! You're good at knowing stuff.
Seniorious is the one Chtholly's compatible with.
And I've got Valgulious.
Seriously, you're extremely well informed.
I bet you checked our equipment
list or something like that.
Actually, no.
They just happen to be swords
I'm familiar with, that's all.
That's all, huh? Very interesting.
Fess up. How much do you really know?
Not much.
I know that you're fairies.
And you fight with dug weapons to protect the world.
I suppose that's about it.
Did the idea of weapons that
look like us bother you at all?
I mean, we're basically disposable lives.
Not to mention, we use relics of those awful emnetwihts.
What's up?
A long time ago,
I knew someone in a similar situation.
And I owe that someone a great deal for many things.
So after hearing your story,
I couldn't just walk away.
Now, you know.
Oh, boy!
A sudden mention of your past!
Two people having a heart-to-heart all alone!
Wait, are you hitting on and or flirting with me?
All alone?
Are you forgetting about the girl on my back?
Course not! Because this is the start of a love
triangle filled with passion, hate, and jealousy.
Keep it down. You're gonna wake her up.
Wow, what a tease.
Willem!
What do you think you're doing in here?
I think I'm taking care of a patient.
Well, who's your patient?
Try not to push yourself.
You do still have a fever.
I'm your caretaker, remember.
So, let me take care.
I don't need you, a caretaker or not.
Besides, what you do for me doesn't really matter anyway.
I appreciate it, but I don't have much time left.
"Time left"?
What does that mean?
Hey...
What is it?
Just um, let's say...
...if I were gonna die in five days, like hypothetically,
do you think you'd be a little nicer to me?
What are you talking about?
In five days, Island Fifteen
will come under a powerful timere attack.
One of the 17 beasts?
None of the beasts can fly.
But a timere can release
parts of its body into the air,
allowing those parts to travel
all the way up to the sky islands.
How do you know for sure it will be five days?
We can predict their attacks, now.
We've fought for centuries. I guess we're bound to evolve.
But it certainly took us long enough!
Apparently, the incoming timere can't
be fought using usual military methods.
However, a fairy wielding a dug weapon...
...can take it out single-handedly.
The only cost would be your life.
That's pretty much it.
If I use my power and Seniorious to blow myself up,
I'll just barely be able to destroy the thing.
How lucky is that, right?
Nobody else will have to die.
Okay, so it's not hypothetical.
Does that maybe make you feel
like granting me a final wish?
Depends on what it is.
Well, I uh...
Um.
Like for example.
What if I...
A kiss?
What if I asked to kiss you?
Just once.
After all that talk about only having five days left,
that's the kind of crap you ask me for?
So what!
Ah!
Ow.
You're a kid. Why are you
trying to be something you're not?
Excuse me?!
What's wrong with wanting to
have sweet memories before I go?
I'm about to die here!
But first, I wanna matter! I wanna
be kept alive in someone else's heart!
Just to be connected.
Tell me! What's wrong with that?
Am I not allowed anything?
I don't want you to sell yourself short, that's all.
You don't have to settle for
who's standing in front of you.
You should buy me while I'm selling myself short.
Seriously, it's a basic rule for shopping smart.
Just go!
If you won't kiss me, don't
try to help! I'm not even crying!
Well, you sound like you're crying.
You're crying!
Good grief. Look, I want you
to turn on your belly for a sec.
I can't hear you.
Will you please stop being difficult?
I said I can't hear you!
Oh, come on.
Could you be any more stubborn?
What... What was that?
Um, I didn't um...
I really didn't feel that one.
I knew it.
You're showing typical symptoms of venenum poisoning.
You generated too much which then gave
you a real nasty case of muscular fever.
This isn't pleasant, but it helps.
Ow! By not pleasant, you mean it feels like fire?!
It'll be better in a little bit.
A little bit?
I'm gonna feel like this forever, aren't I?
Not to worry. You just let me take care of this.
The mightiest brave is here with the mightiest sword.
There's nothing else for you to do.
No.
I can't just walk away.
Next Episode: starry road to tomorrow.