[SOLDIERS chattering]
[SOLDIER 10A groaning]
[NOPHT panting]
[NEPHREN]
It's been a while, Rhantolk.
I'm glad you're all right.
Thanks, the feeling is mutual.
I have to ask, though.
What's with your hair?
Uh, well...
And you. Who are you?
The name's Willem Kmetsch, the
new fairy warehouse caretaker.
It's nice to meet you.
I see that you're
a disfeatured, too.
You aren't, by chance,
a troll, are you?
You mean Nygglatho
has a husband?!
No, she does not!
I'm human.
[NOPHT]
Huh?
[RHANTOLK]
An emnetwiht?
If that's a joke,
it isn't funny.
Well, never mind me.
There's something I
wanna know about you.
[NOPHT gasping]
[laughs]
[NOPHT] Stop it!
That tickles so bad!
I knew it.
She's showing symptoms
of venenum poisoning.
Just try to suck it up.
[NOPHT laughing]
What do you think
you're doing to her?
Relax, it'll be fine.
[RHANTOLK]
How is that "fine"?
[laughs] Ah! My gosh--! Please!
I can't handle this anymore.
Stop! You unhand Nopht
immediately, or else!
Ah!
[NOPHT moaning]
[RHANTOLK whimpers]
I sense dirty thoughts.
[gasps]
[CHTHOLLY grunts]
[RHANTOLK screams]
[WILLEM]
Feel better now?
My body feels so light
it's almost creepy.
I happen to find it unsettling
to have my fatigue disappear
so suddenly like that.
I said you'd be fine.
But how fine was she?!
How fine, what?
Let me guess, you're finding
it hard to trust me, right?
Of course.
You are an emnetwiht.
Others might be able to have
faith in one of the sinners
who destroyed the world,
but I cannot.
Well, I've been surrounded by
those "others" for a while, now.
I must be a very lucky man.
[RHANTOLK] I find your
nonchalance suspicious, as well.
Masking your evil intentions
and tricking people
must be a habit for you.
Yes, I'm grateful you helped
Chtholly survive a battle
in which she was
supposed to die.
However, your being an
emnetwiht raises a flag.
We have no guarantee
you are not dangerous.
Need I remind you
that it was your people
who were responsible
for spreading
the seventeen beasts
across the world?
[WILLEM]
Hm?
[RHANTOLK] A few days
after the beasts appeared,
two islands vanished
from the map.
By the following week,
five countries, four islands,
and two oceans were gone.
The week after that, the world
map had lost all meaning.
And then, before long, all
humanity was wiped out.
[RHANTOLK] How did the beasts
increase so rapidly in number?
[WILLEM] I don't know for sure,
but I've heard they
were originally some kind
of biological weapon.
Biological weapon?
Meaning, they must have used
some organism as a base.
What creature, exactly,
did the humans use
to construct the beasts?
Dunno.
Biological weapons.
That's why they were made.
Their only purpose was to fight.
Like us. We just fight
on the other side.
You don't have to know
everything about them.
They're archenemies who
make you suffer, that's all.
Isn't that right?
I suppose so, but I also wish
to learn the whole truth.
For what it's worth,
I don't mind people like you,
but I gotta walk away
with her so, bye.
I'm sorry about that.
She's usually such a nice girl.
I get her point.
[WILLEM] I'm gonna check
on things out there.
Stay on the ship for me, okay?
[CHTHOLLY]
What? But, I...
Didn't I say not
to push yourself?
Please just stay put.
Don't worry, he's in good hands.
I'll be keeping an eye
on him for you.
Why would you keep
an eye on me?
Obviously, because you had
dirty thoughts about Rhan.
Oh, don't start!
[CHTHOLLY]
Rude.
Always treating me like a kid.
Who cares if Rhan has
a more mature aura.
--[WOLF] All right! Last one!
--[FROGGO] Finally.
[BIRDY]
Which way will it go?
[WOLF]
Now, which one is it?
[SOLDIERS chuckle]
Gotcha!
Oh, come on! Not again!
Ribbit all to hell!
[WOLF] Quit croakin'.
What are you, a baby?
A tadpole? You ain't
got legs down there?
[screams]
Get out of the doorway.
Oh, right, sorry about that.
If it isn't Madam Secretary.
What brings you in here,
sweetheart?
Wanna join us for a drink?
Who knew she'd just be
a disfeatured kid?
Kid or not, she's an
esteemed secretary.
She sure is.
She helps out our honorable
technical officer, in...
...more ways than one.
Hey, would you help us out
in more ways than one, too?
--Just ribbing!
--[SOLDIERS laugh]
You most likely do not
need to worry much
about Nopht and Rantolk.
Neither of them have
ever been the kind
to seriously hate someone.
Yeah. I get it.
Thank you, though.
[WILLEM]
You've always got my back.
I really do appreciate it.
[NEPHREN] I do so because you
might break otherwise.
[WILLEM]
Do I really seem that fragile?
Well, thanks anyway.
And keep looking out for
Chtholly, too, would you?
[NEPHREN]
Mm.
[GRICK]
You moron!
Do you even know
what you've done?!
I know that I'm a first-grade
technical officer.
Not to mention also being the
highest-ranking officer here.
I don't care!
Who died and made you the boss?!
[WILLEM] Well, look who's
as loud as ever.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[GRICK]
Willem!
Oh, good.
Do you know this man,
Second-Grade Officer?
[WILLEM]
Yes.
Okay?
This idiot sent an additional
excavations squad underground.
[MOGDAMAN]
We have to grab as many relics
as possible before we leave.
I don't believe you realize
how crucial this operation is.
Sending too many men
underground at once
is considered a bad idea.
Huh. That's probably
just a silly myth.
It's real! From what
I've been told,
no group of more
than seven salvagers
has ever returned alive!
There's a reason why we
work in small groups.
You must respect the surface!
They've already left, so no
point in complaining now.
All we can do here is
prepare for the worst.
Isn't that right, sir wise
First-Grade Technical Officer?
Yes, you're right
that you're right.
You see how bighearted a
first-grade technical officer
I am? Take care of
those things for me.
[WILLEM]
I will. Thank you, sir.
[sighs]
I wasn't expecting you
of all people to show up.
Well, I wasn't expecting to
see you here. Huh, Grick?
[GRICK]
Huh? Wow, another cutie pie.
Met Nopht and Rhantolk, yet?
You could say that.
You didn't lie, these fairies
really are nice girls.
I'm kinda still in shock.
I won't walk one down the aisle.
Back up, you weirdo.
[WILLEM] Whatever.
So, is the plan to load
the entire haul onto
the Plantajinesta ?
[GRICK] Yep, including
everything on the Saxifraga .
Why?
[WILLEM]
I'm looking for something.
[ARMADILLO] Adviser, we need
your help here, please.
'Kay! I'll see ya later.
You, too, Missy.
--[ALL gasp]
--[CAT] Meow.
[CHTHOLLY]
Done!
[FROGGO]
Ribbit?
[CHTHOLLY laughs]
[ALL gasping]
[WOLF]
Finished.
I'm all done on my end, boss.
[CHTHOLLY]
Thank you!
Well, I did tell her
not to push herself.
[BUNNY] My, if it isn't
the technical officer.
[WILLEM]
Uh?
What brings you all
the way down here?
What, indeed?
Shouldn't you be with your
esteemed secretary?
My esteemed secretary is busy.
Hey, where did you store the
dug weapon that you found?
No idea.
We followed our orders,
which were simply
to carry it back here.
A lot of men were lost
in the attack, y'know.
There's just no way we can
keep track of everything.
'Course not.
[door creaks, slams]
[WILLEM] So, I'm looking
for a needle in a haystack?
[rumbling]
[gasps]
[WORKERS gasping]
[ARMADILLO MAN]
Earthquake?
Careful, boys!
It's a big one today.
There have been a lot
of tremors lately.
[CHTHOLLY gasping]
[CHTHOLLY]
Lil...
Lillia...
Uh.
[LILLIA gasping]
[panting]
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
[screams]
[panting]
Lillia... Asplee...
I'm the brave who is going to
kill you and save the world!
That sounds like it
must be a pain.
[LILLIA]
You have no idea!
And why would you want
to save the world?
[coughs]
I'm doing this for one reason.
It's for my love.
[BOTH gasp]
Time to say goodbye.
Rest in peace!
My name is Chtholly.
I guess I'm still fine.
And here you are.
I can't remember the last time
I had soup this delicious.
Seconds please, oh, dear
Madam Secretary!
Sure! Comin' right up!
This is yummy!
I mean, wow!
The kick of the pepper's
a nice touch,
and the richness of the
texture is next to perfect.
Impressive.
How did Chtholly become
such a good cook?
It's the power of love.
[WILLEM grunts]
Hey, you seem awful mad.
What are ya, scared someone's
gonna take your Chtholly
away from you?
Oh. Hi there, Officer Casanova.
Better make that secretary
of yours happy, you got it?
That girl is gonna
make a perfect wife.
But if you go and
break her heart,
don't make me spell it meowt.
[WILLEM growls]
[GRICK laughs]
[WILLEM]
Screw them!
Perfect wife, my foot!
Make her happy, my ass!
They don't have to tell me,
because I already know.
[gasps] I already know what?
[NOPHT]
Don't start cryin' if you trip.
But since you're reading,
what's that part say?
"Carried the corpse of a god
to the city," I believe.
The text is blurry after that,
so I cannot read it.
Sure hope that god has
mercy on their souls.
[ALL gasping]
[BOTH gasp]
I love it. I just love it.
Thank mew!
You're very welcome.
Who's up next?
[ALL gasping]
[NOPHT, RHANTOLK]
Hm?
Nice work. You're really good
at that, too, Chtholly.
Thanks! I've been working
on a bunch of my skills.
Chtholly, may I ask
you something?
Of course.
Why'd you come to the surface?
Was it perhaps for
that Willem person?
And if so, is that because
he saved your life?
I dunno.
He's rather calm for someone
who's walking a tight rope.
He's certainly awkward,
and he over thinks everything.
The point is, I guess I just...
She just wants to be with him.
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
Ren, c'mon!
Damn him. Damn that man!
She's way too good
for that stupid jerk!
Don't mind them.
I'm rootin' for you two!
Oh, really? So that's
how it is, then?
[CHTHOLLY]
Don't you start with me, too!
[WILLEM sighs]
[NOPHT]
Oh, my!
[WILLEM]
Hm?
Did you sort all of
this out yourself?
[WILLEM]
What are you two doing here?
We've decided to come help.
Looking for that dug
weapon, right?
Really?
What brought this kindness on?
[NOPHT] We've been hearin'
a bunch of stuff about you.
Like that you're taking good
care of the little ones.
Oh, no.
You haven't been told anything
too weird, have you?
[NOPHT] Hm... uh...
You mean like how
you and Chtholly are
close to couple-hood?
Or like how Ithea thinks
you're into young girls?
Never mind! I got it.
Don't think we're doing this
for you. It's for Chtholly.
[gasps] Well, that's nice.
And thanks, but I'm
pretty sure I'll be fine.
[WILLEM]
This is my job.
I kinda want to find it myself.
[WILLEM]
Oh, right.
Bring me your swords, girls.
I'll tune them while I'm at it.
[NOPHT]
What the heck?
[WORKER 10A] What is this?
It wasn't on the list.
[WORKERS murmur]
[rumbling]
[WORKER 10A]
Hm?
[gasping]
[CHTHOLLY]
Hey, there you are.
[WILLEM]
Oh, Chtholly.
What's up?
[CHTHOLLY]
I'm giving out lunch boxes
to those who can't make
it to the mess hall.
I brought this one for you.
Thank you, but the secretary
thing is just an excuse.
You didn't have to.
If I just sat around
doing nothing,
then it would appear that
you really had brought
along your lover instead of
someone with a purpose.
So what? Who cares though?
I happen to care, thank you.
[WILLEM]
Is that so?
[CHTHOLLY]
Is that one Nopht's sword?
Yep, and I found
the other one, too.
[CHTHOLLY]
The "other one"?
[gasps]
[WILLEM]
That's Lapidemsibilus.
I'll have to take a closer look
at it once we get back home.
[CHTHOLLY]
You did it.
You really found it for me.
Do you still remember that night
when I tuned Seniorious?
Or have you forgotten?
I remember.
I also remember who Nephren
and Nopht are, and Rhantolk.
I know her. And I
remember Ithea, too.
I remember them.
Although I'm not sure if I
still remember everything.
I see.
Well, now that we
have the sword,
we don't have to worry about it.
[WILLEM]
Uh?
[gasps] What's the matter?
There isn't anything
wrong with it.
[CHTHOLLY]
Of course there isn't.
If there were, we'd have known
because Nopht would've
been struggling.
No. This sword is known
as the Kinslayer.
And what does the
"Kinslayer" mean?
[WILLEM] It specializes
in killing one's kin,
one's own kind.
You see, this is a sword that
can only be used by humans
to kill other humans.
How can that be when Nopht's
fighting beasts with it?
[WILLEM]
That's exactly why I thought
there must be something wrong.
This sword can only kill humans.
How does she kill
beasts with it? [gasps]
[CHTHOLLY]
Uh. Willem?
It can kill... only humans.
[RHANTOLK]
Meaning, they must have used
some organism as a base.
What creature, exactly,
did the humans use to
construct the beasts?
Oh, God.
[RHANTOLK] A few days after
the beasts appeared,
two islands vanished
from the map.
By the following week, five
countries, four islands,
and two oceans were gone.
The week after that, the world
map had lost all meaning.
And then, before long,
all humanity was wiped out.
[RHANTOLK] How did the beasts
increase so rapidly in number?
[WILLEM]
It can't be...
You don't have to know
everything about them.
They're archenemies who
make you suffer, that's all.
I suppose so, but I also wish
to learn the whole truth.
[WILLEM] That would mean the
ones making the fairies...
The ones making
Chtholly suffer are...
Correct.
And they're not wrong.
Humans did destroy the surface.
[WILLEM gasps]
What's wrong?
[crash]
[gasps]
Willem? Seriously,
what's the matter?
Talk to me!
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[WILLEM]
You're not freaking out?
[CHTHOLLY] For what it's worth,
my heart is about to explode.
But while I don't
know what happened,
you're showing me your
vulnerable side,
which is rare, since you
usually act so tough.
It's not that complicated.
It's my joy plus my desire
for you to be happy.
I feel really lucky.
[WILLEM]
You...
Besides that, you look
like you might vanish
if I left you alone.
Sure, this is embarrassing, but
I'm not going to push you away.
[WILLEM]
You are amazing.
Sorry. I couldn't hear
what you just said.
What was that?
[WILLEM]
Never mind.
Hey, come on!
Please don't be like that!
Say it again.
Just one more time, please.
[WILLEM]
Marry me.
Thank you.
Uh! Wha--?
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
You are what I needed.
You gave me something
that I want to protect.
You gave me a home
I could return to.
You gave me hope.
You gave me a reason to live.
You helped me realize that it's
all right for me to live on.
So, I promise you this...
I swear.
I will make you happy, Chtholly.
[CHTHOLLY] I want to
stay by your side, too.
Now, we can be together forever.
[WORKER 10A whimpering]
[WORKER 10A]
No! N-No, please!
[CHTHOLLY] Next Episode:
evidence of existence.