[CHTHOLLY yells]
[MONSTER 5A groans]
New count.
217!
Yeah, I think
Chtholly's got this.
The rest of us can just go home.
[NEPHREN] The next one
might sprout from inside.
Stay focused, Ithea.
[gasps]
[SOLDIER 5A]
What is that thing?!
[SOLDIER 5B]
I've never seen it before!
[SOLDIERS scream]
[roars]
[CHTHOLLY]
Do you see that?
[NEPHREN]
It isn't a timere.
Maybe it's a new beast.
[ITHEA] I've never seen
anything like it before.
[LIMESKIN]
All hands, retreat.
We've detected the appearance
of a new, unexpected beast.
As such, I'm declaring
this operation a failure.
Island Fifteen is
to be abandoned.
All hands, retreat.
We can't!
Oh no, you don't!
Have you completely lost it?
I promised to stay alive.
I promised to make it home!
I was supposed
to celebrate, too,
and eat all the butter
cake I could handle.
[BOTH gasp]
How I can I do that
if I let this world end!
[NEPHREN]
Chtholly!
[ELQ]
Trees vanishing in morning mist.
[gasps]
[ELQ]
Milk stains. Dazzling petals.
Air mass.
Herring on a wall.
Hedgehog standing on its head.
Organ in a bag.
[CHTHOLLY]
What is this?
[ITHEA]
What could we do?
Whatever that new enemy was,
it sent the whole
battlefield into chaos.
It was ridiculously strong
and we had absolutely
no idea how to fight it.
We had no choice, y'know?
The island had to be abandoned.
[WILLEM]
That sounds awful.
[ITHEA]
It was awful!
Which is why we're all
totally exhausted.
Well, I'm proud of you
for hanging in there.
Success would have cost more
lives than the island was worth.
A strategic defeat.
[ITHEA]
Mm-hm!
But as for your work.
The blades you forged
shone brilliantly, so you are
due our praise and thanks.
Yep, that's right. This
lizard is seriously dead on!
Oh, and I wish you could've been
there to see Chtholly fight,
T.O... It was unbelievable.
The loss was all
my fault, though.
I failed.
I should've just blown myself up
and neutralized the enemy.
But instead, I decided
to be selfish.
You're wrong.
[gasps]
It wasn't you.
The tactical projections failed
to account for the other beast.
If you'd self-destructed
to take it out,
we would've been forced
to try and eliminate
the new one without your help.
That would have yielded
a far worse outcome
than a strategic failure.
Yep. I can't agree more.
It was no one's fault, we never
had a chance to defeat them.
So stop. You don't have
to blame yourself.
Thank you, Ren.
By the way...
What are you two doing?
Willem will feel quite a bit
better if we warm him up.
I'm actually pretty
warm already.
Please get off me.
You're just saying that
to be nice. Not yet.
[yelps] Come on!
A little help over here would
be appreciated, Chtholly.
I bet it would.
[LIMESKIN laughs]
[ITHEA laughs]
[door opens]
Uncle!
[ALL]
Uh, you're her uncle?
Uncle?
Of course not,
she's the daughter
of an old friend of
mine. Now then.
How many times have I told you
not to come here, Phyra?
I am fully prepared to face
the consequences, Uncle.
I sincerely apologize,
but there is no one
for me to turn to but you.
Someone has threatened
to kill Father
if we refuse to cancel next
weekend's ceremony.
Really?
It's because of his
policy as the mayor.
He's trying to ensure
peaceful racial coexistence
within the city.
We're well aware that many do
not look favorably upon that,
but I'm appalled
they would resort
to murder to impede his stance.
Listen. I won't be
able to help you.
Forgive me, Phyra.
But why not?
I have a favor to
ask you, Willem.
I won't.
I have yet to tell you
what it is, though.
Yeah, I can guess what it is.
Let me apologize, now, because
I'm not about to play hero.
Besides that,
I'm up to my neck
in babysitting.
[NEPHREN]
Huh?
Uncle, due to its
sensitive nature,
I would prefer to keep
this between us.
No need to worry.
Now, I can't vouch for
his dependability or
trustworthiness, officially,
but he's earned the
benefit of the doubt.
Right.
[WILLEM] We gotta go.
It's time to pick up Tiat.
Good luck, though. I hope
you find someone to help.
Truly.
Will you at least listen?!
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
At next weekend's ceremony,
my father plans to
unveil a new policy.
It should open the door
for those of all races.
However, the Annihilation
Knights oppose the idea
because they oppose tolerating
anything disfeatured,
so they're plotting
to assassinate him.
I have a feeling they're
seriously gonna regret
that name in five years.
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
They destroy property,
kidnap children,
and assault people.
Their intent is to rid the city
of all disfeatured races,
and they'll seemingly stop
at nothing to do so.
Uh...
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
That's why I felt I had
to request assistance.
Still no.
The Guardian Wings
Military's singular role
is to defend Règles Aile from
any and all external threats.
It is not allowed to interfere
in political affairs of cities.
Archipelago Military Charter,
Chapter Four, Article Three.
This is cruel!
We're clearly in the right,
how can you simply do nothing?
[WILLEM]
Being right doesn't make
the use of force appropriate.
In fact, righteousness
is merely a tool
used for legitimizing
one's own violence.
[gasps]
[WILLEM]
Don't you understand,
the other side feels
the same way.
They believe they're justified
just as much as you
believe you are.
We can't all be right, can we?
That's how wars start.
But I--
Officer Limeskin turned you
down because of this,
and it's why I won't
help, either.
[TIAT]
Nope! It wasn't even
a little scary,
and it didn't hurt!
I laugh in the face
of injections, ha, ha.
I'm so proud of you, Tiat.
We all are.
Thank you, Chtholly!
[WILLEM]
You're not a child, though?
No, I'm not a child!
Sure you're not.
Quick question, T.O.
Don't you think you were awfully
cold to the lovely lady?
Let me guess, it's because
of her age, isn't it?
Like maybe girls older than me
might as well not
be girls, am I right?
No, it's not like that at all.
It doesn't matter whom
I'm dealing with.
I just don't want to
accept anything,
you know, if I can't accept it.
[NEPHREN]
Huh?
Wanna try that again?
Sorry, it sounded
better in my head.
And what's goin' on over
here with you smiling,
what's that about, huh?
Oh, nothing.
I will never understand you two.
I swear!
Uh.
[sniffing]
Something smells really good!
Look, they're wrapping meat
in leaves over there,
and it looks yummy!
[NEPHREN]
It's wrapped ram.
I am pretty hungry,
now that I think about it.
We can grab lunch here,
if everyone wants to.
[PHYRACORLYBIA] I wouldn't
do that if I were you.
They're obviously using
far too much spice,
and they do not have their
permit clearly on display,
as is the legal requirement.
I have little doubt they'll feed
you meat that is barely edible.
If you ask me,
it's not worth the risk.
What's worse, their prices
are higher than normal!
That's worse?
Come this way.
I'll show you genuine
Corna di Luce wrapped ram
that won't make you ill.
That's weird. Did she morph
into someone else?
Maybe.
[TIAT]
So good!
[ITHEA]
I can't stop wolfing it down!
Let me see, if I had to guess,
I'd say they used less spice
and incorporated some herbs
to give this wrap a
little more balance.
Either way, the flavor makes it
easy to eat a whole bunch of it.
I know, it's so, good!
[WILLEM]
What's wrong?
You haven't taken a single bite.
[gasps] Just thinking.
Well, don't force yourself.
I'm sure the girls
will take any leftovers.
[BOTH]
We sure will!
You may not know this, but
wrapped ram is a tradition here.
And this restaurant makes the
best wraps in the entire city!
Of course, all the locals
know about this place.
Even a five-year-old
would tell you that.
Wow, the local five-year-olds
are intense.
To top it off, where we
are is so legendary,
countless movies have been
filmed right here!
Oh! Like the scene in
Clockwork Love and Dreams,
where the golem
accidentally gets drunk!
That's right!
You know, I think I've also seen
it before in Let Me Trick You,
and The Return of Detective
Curio , and Howl, Lazioni !
My, how delightful.
I am very impressed!
As for us, our
ten-year-old's intense.
My beautiful Corna di Luce.
It's been the setting
for many, many stories.
No surprise, though.
The rich cuisine, featuring
classics like wrapped ram,
and the artistry, history
and luminaries are
all well known to those
across Règles Aile now.
I'm just so proud of it!
Wow, I can tell you
really love this city,
like a whole lot, don't you?
Yes. Corna di Luce
is my home, after all.
I suppose it's my
favorite city ever!
Ha, ha! I like that
because I love it, too!
[WILLEM laughs]
Favorite ever, huh.
I'm impressed you can say
that with a straight face.
And what does that mean?
Nothing. I like your
style, that's all.
I just wasn't sure we'd ever
get you to lighten up.
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
Don't mock me.
I hate it when people
always speak casually.
I gathered as much. [laughs]
Whaddaya think. Somethin'
weird in her past, right?
Maybe?
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
This is Perjurer's Grave.
A legendary con man from
around 200 years ago
rests in this location.
I've seen this in movies, too!
Of course you have.
The stone says,
"Here lies an honest man."
I know this is gonna
be a bit off topic,
but how did we end up
on a sightseeing tour?
Is there a problem?
We have time until the airship's
ready to take us home.
[ITHEA] It's just kinda weird
to take weapons sightseeing.
I mean, talk about
special treatment!
If you ask me, we better thank
the lizard and the lady.
[trumpet, accordion play]
[ELQ]
Locked red grimoire.
Sweet cry of death.
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[ELQ] Headless clown,
wandering in twilight.
He laughs, laughs, laughs,
laughs, laughs, laughs.
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[whimpering]
[WILLEM]
Chtholly?
[CHTHOLLY]
Wh-What is it?
Are you sure you're
feeling all right?
You've been so quiet today, it's
like having a statue among us.
As far as quiet goes,
statues are the quietest.
If you're too tired, please
tell me you're too tired.
I don't want to push you
and make it worse.
Right.
It isn't like that, though.
Didn't mean to worry you.
I'm sorry.
If the venenum your body
generated during combat
is still lingering
somewhere inside you,
do want me to do the deal again?
No, thanks!
And will you please stop doing
that, you're freaking me out!
What's the deal?
None of your business,
so back off!
Next up, we have the
Lovers' Staircase.
This is where a legendary couple
whose love transcended
social status met.
[TIAT] I've seen this
in so many movies!
Yes, of course she has.
The two accidentally bumped
into each other at the top.
They rolled down
the stairs together,
marking the start of
their romance, but now...
[ITHEA]
There's a "no rolling" rule?
[BOTH gasp]
You mean we can't
roll down the stairs?!
[PHYRACORLYBIA laughs]
[gasps] Hey.
All right, it's time
to set the bait.
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
Well, what do you think?
Do you like the city so far?
Yes, I'm enjoying my time here.
I already loved it, but now
I like love, love, love it!
[WILLEM]
That's wonderful.
Hey, is there a fun
spot we can head to
that's a bit more
isolated than this?
I know just the place.
Welcome to the Well of Wishes.
[TIAT] Oh! I've never
ever seen this before!
[ITHEA]
The Well of Wishes?
Hold on, is this one of
those throw your coin in,
and get your wish granted
kind of places?
That sounds like it came
straight out of a fairy tale!
[THUG 5A] Forgive us for
interrupting your fun,
but your tour has
come to an end.
[THUG 5A chuckles]
[NEPHREN]
We're surrounded.
What are you doing?
Who are you people?
Oh, come on, you can't
tell me you don't know
the Annihilation Knights
when they appear!
[THUGS]
Annihilate! Destroy!
Annihilate! Destroy...
So it is you!
Really...?
Apparently.
We have come here
for all that is right
and for the greater good,
we must assassinate the mayor,
assassinate the mayor
for all that is right
and for the greater good!
As an insurance policy,
we will take you into custody,
take you into custody
as an insurance policy!
He talks weird.
All that effort for
such an awful show.
[PHYRACORLYBIA] You disgust me,
there are children present!
[THUG 5A]
Ha, ha! Those filthy disfeatured
cannot understand
our righteousness,
our righteousness. Those filthy
disfeatured cannot understand!
Now, hear me!
For the sake of all I
know and believe right,
I shall not give in
to the likes of you!
Take her.
[THUGS yell]
Not yet.
Bang!
Ow!
[thud]
[gasps]
--Bang.
--[groans]
Bang.
[groans]
Bang!
[neighs]
Bang.
[OX THUG groans]
[PHYRACORLYBIA gasping]
What just happened here?!
[WILLEM] First of all, I've
known you've been following us.
So we kept to
rather public places.
When we moved to a desolate one,
you saw your chance,
but you never had one.
Please don't tell me.
Did you use me to lure them in?
[WILLEM] Yes. You were
what's called bait.
To be clear,
I could not care less
about either your
politics or justice.
I'm only taking your side
for personal reasons.
You've been extremely
kind to us,
and it helps that the little
ones seem to love this city.
Uh! Whoa.
Who would've known
our precious T.O.
could be one scary man.
A con man.
This is how he actually is.
Know your place, disfeatured,
disfeatured, know your place.
[WILLEM]
Bang!
[crash]
Try to hide that bloodlust.
You're pros?
[THUG 5A gasping]
Damn! Move it, boys!
Boys, move it right now!
[THUG 5A whimpers]
[GOLEM 5A]
Cease and desist.
--[GOLEMS] Arrest. Arrest.
--[GOLEM 5C] Cease and desist.
[GOLEMS]
Arrest. Arrest...
Cease and desist.
[THUG 5A sighs]
[WILLEM chuckles]
Willem kind of seems
like a bad guy.
Well, he does happen
to be the sole survivor
of the terrifying
emnetwiht race, so...
[NEPHREN]
Con man.
[smack]
[WILLEM groans]
I may be extremely
grateful for your help,
but I, I simply cannot
accept your methods!
All right. I figured
as much, though.
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
Also, I've been trying not
to bring this up again,
but upon our initial meeting,
you touched my belly.
[WILLEM]
Huh...?
[PHYRACORLYBIA]
Don't play dumb with me!
To us lycanthropos,
our bellies are sacred places
that we may only reveal
to our spouses.
Ah, okay?
I hate you with every
ounce of my being!
[sighs]
Thank you so much, girls.
I hope you come back to
visit us again someday!
[bell tolls]
It is a beautiful city.
[WILLEM]
I can see why the lady
wanted to protect her home
with such, uh... passion.
[CHTHOLLY]
Yes.
But she hates me, and it
seems she hates me a lot.
I imagine she'd probably rather
not ask me for any help again.
[WILLEM]
It's for the best, though.
She's genuine,
and people like that should
be able to stay that way.
[CHTHOLLY]
You're ridiculous.
Excuse me?
The finger guns were nothing
more than camouflage.
Sure, you attacked them, but
you did it by throwing coins.
Good eye, Chtholly.
[CHTHOLLY]
It's not a good eye.
I just most likely know your
fighting style and strength
better than anyone else in
this world, or any other.
Did you forget?
I could see it because
you taught me to fight
in the exact same way.
I paid attention.
Yes, you certainly did.
I think you were
such a good student
you may have made me forget.
Temporarily.
Tell me, you wanted a fight.
[WILLEM gasps]
[CHTHOLLY] I don't know
what you're trying to do,
but I wish you'd stop.
You don't have to fight anymore.
You're no longer alone.
We've taken on all of your
battles, so you're free.
I'm extraordinarily grateful.
For years, I've waited
for death to release me.
While I've waited, all I wanted
was to go back home,
to go back to the people
that waited for me.
But after meeting
you all, it seems
well, I've changed a little.
I started to feel happy.
I wanted a home again.
Meeting you has brought
me a slice of salvation,
and when you returned alive,
that brought me...
Well, it's like a joy
I'd been missing.
[gasping]
Hang on, don't try to back
away from me like that!
Come on, don't look at me
as if I'm embarrassing you!
I'm tryin' to be nice here!
Okay, whatever.
I was surprised you
noticed, and I'm done.
[CHTHOLLY laughs]
[CHTHOLLY]
How could I not?
I'm in love with you.
[ITHEA]
Finally! We get to go home!
Aw, I wanted to check out
a couple more places.
Remember, you're a
fairy soldier now.
So, I'm positive you'll get
the chance to come back.
True! You're so right!
[gasps]
You are Technical Officer Willem
Kahmesh, is that correct?
Yes, and who might you be?
First-Grade Officer
Burohnny Maxi.
I'm military police.
Interesting.
I see Officer Limeskin's
report was quite accurate.
"A tall, black-haired
disfeatured.
Likely has a thing
for young girls."
Nah, if he actually did,
someone I know wouldn't always
have such a tragic expression.
Am I right, Chtholly?
There is an individual I'd very
much like for you to meet.
Come with me.
[WILLEM] No, thank you.
I have plans already.
[BURONNY]
It's Souwong Kahndel.
[NEPHREN]
Willem?
[WILLEM]
I'm sorry.
I can't walk away after
hearing that name.
[gasps]
[WILLEM]
Burohnny, was it?
Yes.
I need to ask a favor,
take care of these girls.
I can most definitely do that.
Wait a second!
I won't let you stay here!
We make you happy.
Come back home!
I can't go, not just yet.
If you stay,
I'll get really angry!
Chtholly...
I won't let you stay!
You jerk. You're a big jerk!
[CHTHOLLY cries]
I'm so sorry.
[CHTHOLLY]
Come back.
I'll be waiting, so you'd
better come home, okay?
Yeah. I will come home.
I swear that I will.
Good.
It's a promise.
[WILLEM] I never welcomed
them back from battle.
I probably shouldn't say this,
but you make the
most peculiar face
when you cry, Officer Kmetsch.
[smack]
[WILLEM] Next Episode:
no news was good news.