♪
(singing in Japanese)
Please be careful, sir.
The streets are dangerous
this time of night.
Won't you allow me
to get a rickshaw for you?
There's no moon to light
your way home tonight, sir.
You forget that I'm
a government official,
a respected member
of the ruling party
and there's no one I fear.
Young man, the day
someone dares to attack me,
they'll find out how
sharp my teeth really are.
Good night!
As you wish.
Good night, sir.
Tonight, all your teeth
will get yanked out, Takamori.
(chuckles)
♪
All right, men,
what is this?
Hey!
♪
Huh?
Speak up!
Who the hell are you?
The Kenwadan gang.
You'd better get out of the way!
I've had enough,
you leave me no choice
but to kill you.
Just relax, sir.
I'll take care of
these masked cowards.
♪
Now it's time for you
to give me the key, Takamori.
Key?
What key?
I don't know about any key.
Oh, come on, now.
Let's not pretend.
I know that you have it.
You want to live,
so you'd better
give it to me.
I mean business.
♪
What a stupid, stubborn ox.
Huh?
Hey, that dog's got the key!
Stop!
Damn you!
We've got him!
Don't let him get away.
We got him now.
I'll get him.
Huh?
(police whistle)
Damn, it's the police!
Run!
I humbly ask for your help.
My luck has really taken
a turn for the worse
since we've come back
from our long trip to Edo.
Please grant me good luck
when it comes to throwing
the dice.
Six-five!
I will give you
a generous offering
after I win.
Just run a tab
and lemme know
what I owe ya.
Huh?
My gosh, what is it?
It's way too big to be a dog
and it's too furry to be a cow.
At least it's breathing.
I guess it is a dog.
All right, Fido, take it easy!
I'm warning ya,
I am not a meal ticket!
Now, mind you,
I love animals,
especially dogs,
after all, I've dated a few,
but if you think I'm
falling for a big furry dog
with soulful eyes,
you've got another
thing coming, buster!
Would you let go?
Oh, boy!
Rice cakes!
Delicious!
I had a patient
that paid me in rice,
so I thought I'd share.
Thanks, I'll get us some tea.
How sweet.
It's nice you think of us.
I can be very giving.
Hey, Megumi,
am I glad you're here.
Do me a favor and take
a look at this dog.
What?
Sano, that's a bear!
No, Yoshi, it's a dog.
Wow, can we keep him?
Say, "Bow-wow," doggy!
"Bow-wow," boy.
Sano, I never knew
you had a pet dog.
When did this happen?
Where have you
been keeping him?
What's his name?
He just found me.
Well, you make
a lovely couple.
So now, you brought
this animal back here
and you're expecting
me to examine him?
Well, you should be able
to take a look at this dog.
You call yourself
a doctor, don't you?
I'm a doctor, but it's hard
to believe you call yourself
a man.
Please, Miss Megumi,
help us to find out what's wrong
with Sano's newfound friend.
He's not my friend!
Well, considering how rudely
you've been acting
towards me, Sano,
I shouldn't help you.
But since Kenshin
asked me so nicely,
I'll do it.
You surprise me, Sano,
I thought all you care
about is eating for free,
gambling, and having
a warm place to sleep.
Don't you see this dog
forced me to help him?
Well, we better
take him out back
and let Megumi
have a look at him.
I've lifted water buffalos
that weighed less
than this thing.
Susie, maybe we can help
nurse this dog back to health
and then, he'll be
out pet forever!
Sure, Bow-wow better.
So, Sano, I guess this dog
isn't your pet after all.
The only pets I've ever had
was when I lived by the dump
and those were
cockroaches and fleas!
And his pet fleas still
live with him today.
So, tell us, Megumi,
what's the story
on our new friend?
He's overtired and starved,
but he'll be fine.
He had water in his lungs,
it looks like he almost drowned.
I'd say he had a rough
couple of days and he might
have accidentally
fallen into the river.
All he needs now
is food and rest.
Megumi, why don't you take
a break and have some of
that black oolong tea
that I made for us.
Yeah, let's eat,
'cause there's nothing
that tastes better
with tea than Megumi's
ohagi rice.
She makes the best
rice balls in town!
They do look delicious.
Thank you, let's eat!
Well.
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Those are mine!
Look, he wants you to share!
Good dog!
Well, now, it looks like
your canine companion
wants to split your lunch.
Bon appetit, Sano!
He's not a friend!
Help me get this tub
of lard off my lap
before he makes really
short work of my lunch!
Oh, no, is he drooling?
He is drooling!
Oh, that's just great.
Now, I've got a rice ball feast
that's been covered
in doggy drool.
The first good meal I get
in weeks and this fleabag
reduces it to spitballs.
He's going after them!
And I thought I was
a good chow hound!
I got him!
I don't got him!
Yoshi, do me a favor
and help me out here!
Okay!
♪
Unbelievable.
My gosh, they're all gone.
Oh, boy, he ate the whole tray
without even coming up for air!
You know, you are
gonna pay for that!
Are you trying that
soulful eyes routine on me?
He's expressing he's grateful.
I think he's trying
to express that he wants
more food.
I'd say that this dog
must be related to Sano
because even after he's eaten,
he still wants more.
Hardy-har-har.
If you like that
chow you just ate,
there's only one way to get it.
If you want more,
you gotta go straight
to the source.
But you gotta ask
Megumi extra nicely.
Hey, what are you up to?
He must like you
to drool on your pants!
Finally, a little
of your own medicine.
That'll teach you two.
You sure would make
a good dog trainer.
He sure likes people.
He's too friendly
of a dog to have grown up
on the street.
He's someone's pet.
that's for sure,
and the family
he lives with has got
to be missing him a lot.
Let's make a drawing of him
and post it on the street
so they'll be reunited.
Oh, Kenshin,
you always come up
with such great ideas.
Are you okay, Sano?
Yup.
So, just what is this
doggy's name anyway?
I don't know.
Let's give him a name.
Since he's so big,
why don't we call him Husky?
Husky?
How about Furball?
Husky sounds like a perfect name
and, while we're at at,
let's give Sano a new name.
Let's call him Musky.
Okay, Husky, go get her, boy!
(laughter)
(growling)
Sanosuke, I'll get you for this!
The coast is clear, sir.
As all of you know,
we've been searching
for that dog.
Any leads yet?
We've combed all
the streets, sir,
but there's no sign
of him anywhere.
We know the police are close
to figuring out our scheme.
We must fine
the dog with the key.
Do whatever it takes.
Understood?
Understood, sir!
♪
So, Sano, did you put
all those notices up?
Yeah, I posted every one
of those "Found Dog" drawings
from here to
the outskirts of town.
All mine are up.
Great, now in a day or two,
his owner will
come to claim him.
Miss Kaoru, we're home!
Husky, you come back here,
you four-legged terror!
What is going on here?
I'll tell you what's going on:
That dog isn't housebroken.
He's gone in almost every
corner of this house.
It smells gross!
He's just marking his territory,
It's really natural
for a dog to do that.
All dogs do it.
That's true.
Anyway, in spite of all this,
I made dinner.
So, I hope you boys
brought your appetites.
Oh, no.
Say it ain't so.
Kaoru made us dinner?
I asked Kaoru to cook
dinner for us because I knew
we'd be busy
posting those flyers.
How could you do that to us?
Come on.
Eating her food's like
being sentenced to die.
Oh, no, who ruined
my beautiful dinner?
It's all gone!
Maybe Husky might've--
Of course it must've been Husky!
He must've been hungry
to eat all that food.
Oh, well, what can you do?
Hungry?
You've gotta be kidding.
An animal would have
to be downright starving
to eat any food
that Kaoru cooks.
What did you just say?
Kaoru, just calm down.
Tell you what,
I'll make everyone
a delicious meal.
But you do like my cooking,
isn't that right?
Sure, not even you like
Kenshin's cooking better, right?
Who asked you?
Sano, after dinner tonight,
you take that dog home with you
or so help you, I'll
cook for you for a week!
Okay, I'll do it, I promise.
♪
Hey, what do you think this is?
Doggy Heaven?
Now, you get out
of my bed, Husky,
before I turn you into
a plush throw rug!
Move!
I see, so you wanna
do this the hard way!
(grunting)
♪
What's that racket?
I'm sorry he woke you.
It's just for tonight.
I promise to keep him quiet.
Please go back to bed.
Good night.
♪
Well, looks like
we've found you.
Huh?
You brought Husky?
I had to.
You see, last night,
he made such a racket
that I'll get kicked
out of my place if he's
over there again.
Please let him
stay here, Kaoru?
All right, he can stay.
Why are you
carrying him like that?
It's like this:
Whenever I try to get him
to walk, he knocks me over,
so I thought carrying him
might be the easiest thing.
And now that I've lost that dog,
I can go play some dice!
I'll borrow some money
and then it's time
for six-five!
One, two, three, four!
One, two, three!
Look, Husky popped a bubble!
(laughter)
♪
Husky's certainly
behaving himself today
and the girls just
love having him around.
Bye, girls!
I'm leaving now!
There, now I think I'll take
a little break for a while.
Hey, Kenshin!
Can I help you
with something, Yoshi?
You have a pretty
serious look on your face.
I have a serious
question for you.
Would you please give me
a sword fighting lesson?
Well?
Sure, why not?
You really mean it?
Sure I mean it.
Great!
Don't move, I'll
go get my sword!
Wait, Yoshi, I can't until
I finish doing the wash!
Oh, I hope he won't
be too let down.
How could I have forgotten it?
Kenshin, I forgot the package
I need to deliver to Mr. Suzuki
at the marketplace.
have you seen it
around here, by chance?
No.
Hey, Kaoru, did you happen
to see my bamboo sword anywhere?
Is it in the dojo?
Maybe a thief came
and stole your sword?
Who would wanna
steal a bamboo sword?
They always say two sets
of eyes are better than one,
so I'll take a look, too.
Oh, thanks, Kenshin.
I couldn't have
misplaced that package.
Maybe it was stolen, too.
But we've never had anything
stolen from here before.
That's true, but there's
a first time for everything,
even bad things.
Unless...
What's bothering you?
A minute ago, there were
wet clothes in this bucket.
Look at those footprints.
♪
Husky, you're a bad boy!
So, you're the thief
we've been looking for!
My poor slippers,
they were shiny and new,
but not now!
There's teeth marks on my sword!
Agh!
I just can't
forgive him for this!
Husky, now you're asking for it!
♪
That's some dog.
He probably thinks humans
are here for him to tease.
He probably thinks he's
going to get away with this!
Well, I say, no way!
You're right,
it's time for a showdown!
Right now!
♪
Well, at least he didn't hurt my
Reverse Dead Sword in any way.
Hmm?
Come back!
Let me get a hold of you!
You furry creep!
It's all over for you, Husky!
Freeze, or it's a bamboo enema!
Why in the world
did he just stop?
Well, maybe he sees something.
Yeah, but what?
Huh?
We'd better keep it
quiet and let them nap.
I think you're right, Kaoru.
Tiptoe, tiptoe.
Quietly, softly.
Charge!
♪
What a streak of bad luck.
No hits.
I bet I couldn't hit
a wall with my fist.
Hey, Kaoru, I'm back.
♪
As usual, you're full of energy.
Yeah, Husky's so energetic
that we can't handle him.
Yeah, he's really gotta go.
Huh?
What did he do
that got you two
so worked up?
All that matters is that
I will never let that dog
near my house again, understand?
Isn't that a
little harsh, Kaoru?
If you don't like it,
you don't have to come
back here either.
(grunts)
What am I gonna do with you?
This is getting tough.
♪
Kenshin, come on!
When are you gonna
give me that lesson?
Yoshi, I'm telling you,
first I have to finish
the laundry.
Excuse me, Mr. Himura,
we need to talk.
Why, Police Chief Ono.
That's right, I just saw this.
I see, Sano, you're
at your wits end,
so you decided
to bring the dog here.
Yeah, I am literally
begging for your help, Megumi.
Fine, just leave him
right over there.
Husky can stay here for now.
Gee, thanks a lot, Megumi!
That really takes
a load off my mind
and my back.
See ya!
Excuse me, doctor,
but does that tall man
happen to be your lover?
Huh?
There's no way
I'd even touch him!
(groaning)
Husky, just stay here.
Behave yourself and don't
get into mischief, okay?
I'll find your master,
I promise you.
♪
The Kenwadan Gang?
Yes, they are a secretive group
who present themselves
as activists for freedom
and civil rights,
but in reality,
they are hooligan
thugs who extort money
to further their
subversive agenda.
Earlier this week,
they killed three men
and made off with the key
to a security chest.
And just where have
your sources told you
the key is now?
Your dog friend had it last.
This chest belonged
to the civil servant
killed in the robbery.
We know it contains
secret papers with
sensitive information about
local political officials.
So, the Kenwadan gang
want the key so they
can blackmail these officials,
extort money, and then
gain political control.
They know that
dog has the key
and I'm sure they're
searching desperately for it.
That explains
who that guy was.
Kenshin!
Excuse me, but I
must go warn Sano.
He's with the dog.
Husky?
Husky!
He must've wandered
off somewhere.
With all those posters
we've put up and as many people
as I've asked about him,
maybe we're mistaken?
Maybe Husky's
from another town.
Huh?
Husky!
♪
Easy, easy!
How many times have I told
you to cut that crap out!
Give us the dog
and we'll let you live!
And just who
exactly are you?
That doesn't matter to you.
We'll just take that dog
and you go on your way, got it?
By the way you're talking,
I know you're
not Husky's master.
(growling)
Well, from the
sound of his growl,
I get the feeling he hates
you guys as much as I do.
Maybe even a little more.
Let me kill him.
So, are you ready for
the terror of the Kenwadan gang?
I've heard of your group.
The style you use is kempo.
That's enough, Husky.
You'd better move out, boy,
'cause things could get scary.
♪
Huh?
How do you like that?
He's never listened
to me before and when
I really need him, he runs!
Get that dog!
Don't let him get away!
I can't let you do that.
Sano?
Sano!
I guess that he hasn't
returned here yet.
I hope he isn't gambling.
Oh, that reminds me.
Hmm?
I wanna ask a special
favor of you, Yoshi.
I don't want you telling Kaoru
about this Kenwadan business.
Okay, I won't say anything
if you don't want me to,
but why?
I should have never told Kaoru
all about Shishio and his gang.
It made her a nervous
wreck for months.
Everything's so nice
now and she's so happy.
I just don't want us
to make her nervous.
Oh, you worry too much.
No, I just care about her.
Hey, it's Husky!
Well, at least he's okay.
Hey, what is it, boy?
Sanosuke!
♪
I can't believe they
didn't fight better.
Well, they are good
for curing insomnia.
Okay, your turn, kitty-face.
I have the heart of a lion
and the teeth of a tiger.
Hey, here's a nice souvenir,
it'll be a hit at parties!
You've taken your last breath.
♪
Good night!
Looks like the party's
over for you, buddy.
(barking)
How do you like that?
Husky brought some backup!
Hmm?
Oh, he wrecked it!
So, those thugs
were after Husky
because they
thought he had a key?
Right, but we haven't found it.
I know this might sound strange,
but could I borrow
your glasses for a minute?
Well, if you must,
then, of course.
So, what do you
expect to happen?
Just watch and maybe
you'll learn something.
Hey, where's he taking them?
Come on, we've gotta follow him!
Now I think I see what
you're up to, Himura!
This might work.
I still don't get it.
My reversed-edge sword helped me
figure this out...I think.
How did your sword help you?
You'll see.
All right, it's working
out like I thought.
Oh, it's the key!
Good detective work, Mr. Himura.
By the way, the dog's
master saw your notice
and he's looking forward
to having his dog back.
We'll come by
for him tomorrow.
Great!
Once again, we sincerely thank
all three of you for your help.
I only wish there were
more citizens like you
who weren't afraid
to take a stand
against such riffraff
as those hoodlum gangs.
Right, Husky?
Congratulations, Sano.
Thanks to your dogged efforts,
they found Husky's owner.
I'm just hoping Kaoru
will let Husky spend
the night here.
Sure, why wouldn't she?
If it isn't
the Wanderer himself!
Huh?
Kaoru?
I come back from teaching
and not only is
all our laundry
lying in the dirt,
but there's no dinner ready!
No one left me a note
saying where you went
and the house is
a complete mess!
We are outta here!
You have some serious
explaining to do!
I'm sorry, Miss Kaoru, but I--
Maybe you better just listen!
So, that's why you
brought him this time?
Umm-hmm.
We'll you can go ahead
and leave him here.
You are the best!
Good.
Sano looks kinda hungry.
Would it be okay
if we had him stay
for dinner, too?
You mean it?
I suppose we have
enough food for three more.
Why did you say
"three more," Miss Megumi?
Because Sanosuke eats
enough for three people.
Hey, now!
(laughter)
Now say, "Ah!"
Sano, open up, say "ah!"
You may not be lucky at dice,
but when it comes to food,
you're very lucky
and you're surrounded
by pretty girls to boot.
Boy, Husky, I really
owe you for this one!
You know, after dinner,
you could repay me with
a nice foot massage.
Why stop at your feet?
I heard that.
♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪ It's gonna rain ♪
♪
♪ It's gonna rain ♪♪