♪
(fire blazing)
This has gone on
far too long.
Prepare yourself,
Battousai, to die!
Argh!
(whoosh)
Oh!
You're helpless
against my power!
(laughs)
Prepare yourself!
Ahh!
♪
(yelling)
Die, Shishio!
Ahh!
Huh?
Ugh!
Ahh!
You, you murdering bastard!
Is that right?
I beg to differ!
Now join your dead friend!
Ugh!
(yelling)
Oh!
Ahh!
♪
(laughs)
-Don't celebrate yet.
-Hmm?
Don't you think it's
a bit early for that?
Well, look what the cat drug in.
Sorry, but I'm not in the mood
to fight a loser.
(wind blowing faintly)
Shishio had devastated our side.
The carnage in his wake
was gruesome.
It appeared he had
defeated our allies
single-handedly,
and it looked
like our cause was lost.
Sano had done what he could
to no avail,
as well as our friend Saito,
but they couldn't
overpower Shishio
and save Kenshin.
Unless a miracle occurred,
Aoshi would have
to be our only chance.
Aoshi, why don't you
go back to your mama-san
and don't let me see
your pathetic face again.
I can't waste my precious time
on a worthless warrior like you.
Aoshi, give up
before you get hurt.
Besides, you let
Battousai beat you,
there's no reason
for you to even be here,
this battle's for winners!
Get it?
You had the chance
to be the most powerful
but you blew it,
so why don't you
turn around and
get out of here?
Go!
Sorry, but I disagree with you.
I'm perfectly
aware that I lost.
Battousai never
avoided a battle,
and neither should
Shishio, I'll tell you why.
You're claiming victory
under false pretenses.
I wounded Battousai,
and as a result,
he lost much of his strength.
He wasn't able to fight you
at his full strength.
You can't claim the title
of most powerful
when you defeat a man
in a depleted condition,
it's meaningless.
And he's a sore loser at that!
Just what is he proposing to do?
I believe the man
wishes to compensate
for Battousai's loss
by competing with me.
That's ridiculous,
he wouldn't have had
a chance in Hell,
even if he'd been
in excellent condition.
It's obvious to me
that your power
outweighs his.
It really doesn't matter
what kind of shape he was in,
you would've won!
But I think
we should let him try.
What?
I accept your challenge, Aoshi.
Although I think
it's a foolish choice
on your part,
it affords me
the perfect opportunity
to show the world
who's really most powerful.
My win over Battousai has
already earned me that title,
but a defeat over you
would be icing on the cake.
I only hope that you will
give me a challenge,
I don't like being bored.
And if by some miracle
you should win,
you can gloat all you want
to your dead Oni gang comrades.
Huh!
(metallic chime)
(whoosh)
♪
Your parlor tricks
are worthless!
Now your life is over!
Please, you're too slow,
I can see right through you
you stupid fool!
I wouldn't be so sure.
(swords clanging)
Aoshi's spending
all of his energy
trying to defend himself!
Shishio is an absolutely
brilliant tactician,
he would make a great leader
for all of Japan!
(clang)
How is Aoshi holding his own
against Shishio?
Battousai thrashed him
to the point that
he could barely stand up!
He used the same technique
on Aoshi that he used
to defeat Sojiro!
It's a miracle he's alive,
let alone standing up
to Shishio!
How can he have so much energy?
It's not possible!
Ahh!
Hit me with your best shot!
Heh!
(panting)
Why is Aoshi taking
such an insane risk?
He's already been
defeated by Battousai!
Could it be that
he's still obsessed
with becoming most powerful?
(grunting)
You've had it now.
Was that your best, Aoshi?
I expected more from you.
(laughs)
Hah, your reign
of terror is over!
You're nothing but a burned out
shell of a man.
Let's see if you can
handle this technique!
Oh, I can handle it.
But can you handle me?
(grunting)
♪
(coughing)
Your cross sword technique
is child's play to me.
♪
Aoshi, what made you think
that an unsophisticated move
like that would ever work on me?
To win this one,
you'll have to do
a lot better than that!
(laughs)
(whoosh)
Why don't you give up while
you still have the chance?
Yah!
Ugh!
(laughs)
Why are you waiting?
He's behind him,
but he doesn't attack.
Are you facing some kind
of moral dilemma, Aoshi?
Because if you are,
it would be a shame.
Not only have
you got me cornered,
but you're behind me as well.
Why are you just standing there?
It's the perfect time
for you to kill me.
What's the matter
with you Aoshi,
attack!
Why don't you have the nerve
to go ahead and do it?
Your taunts won't
distract me, Shishio.
I'll attack you
on my own terms.
For all of those
that you have slain
in the name of
the Juppongatana.
Shishio!
Kaiten Kenbu Rokuren!
(yelling)
♪
Too late!
Huh!
Kaiten Kenbu Rokuren
is very effective
when it's done correctly,
but I'm afraid you may
have missed a beat!
It's unfortunate for you,
because you came so close,
but I was quicker
and my move
made yours obsolete.
Only a master can be
truly successful at it,
and you'll never
achieve that level!
It's impossible to beat me!
Ha ha!
Ugh!
(whooshing)
(thud)
It's really a tragedy,
you had so much
going for you, Aoshi.
But apparently,
you've allowed yourself
to be corrupted
by your own
worthless demons.
You're completely defeated,
now there's no
use in you moving.
Unless Battousai decides
to get up and save you!
What?
That's a ridiculous notion.
Why, Battousai will never
be able to get up again.
(laughs)
If that's what you're expecting,
Aoshi, then you've gone crazy.
Battousai's practically
a corpse.
He's never going
to get up again!
All he's good for now
is food for the worms.
There's no sense in
continuing the struggle,
it's useless!
Face it, Aoshi,
Battousai is never
going to come back to life,
so why don't you just forget it?
I hope that he listens,
Shishio won't be able
to fight any longer.
Ugh...
Can Battousai really be dead?
(clang)
My master once told me
the will to live
is stronger than anything else.
His enlightened words
have given me the power
and strength to continue on,
even when I was hovering
between the void
of life and death.
All I can tell you
is that my mastery
of the secret principle
is based on this belief.
The crimes I committed
as Battousai
can never be forgiven,
and so I've made up my mind
that it doesn't matter
if I live or die.
That's not important, right?
No.
I realize that
I deserve to be
punished for
the heinous sins
of my past.
But no matter
how much guilt I feel,
or how much pain
I've caused other people
by committing these
terrible offenses,
there's still
a powerful feeling
deep inside of me
that makes it possible
to survive!
It's the will,
the desire
to go on living.
And never, ever giving up.
That will is
my greatest secret,
Aoshi.
(panting)
Look, the man isn't
going to give up!
Why does he keep fighting?
His efforts will be futile!
I'm beginning to believe
he's possessed!
Don't be so hasty, Shishio.
I'm still willing
to take you on.
I'll finish you yet!
What a pity!
You remind me of Battousai,
I'd have to say that
you're more intolerant
than he is, but
you're just like him
when it comes to taking up
the sword for others.
Don't like hearing the truth?
Personally, I believe
you have the guts or the will
to become the most powerful!
And just like that
pathetic Battousai,
your desire to live
was already gone
when you came here
to fight me!
(whoosh)
It doesn't make a whole
lot of difference to me
whether you compare me
to Battousai or not,
but there is one thing
I have to say.
Listen to me, Shishio,
because I really believe this.
I'm more powerful than you are.
(wind rushing)
Hmph, you're desperate, Aoshi.
It sounds like the
howling of a dying dog.
Hmm?
There's no way, it can't be,
I killed him!
(grunting)
(wind rushing)
Battousai is alive!
Oh, no, that's impossible!
He'd have to be immortal.
But just the same,
Shishio, he appears
to be unconscious,
now's your chance
to get rid of him for good!
Go ahead and give him
the final blow
while you still can,
then you will own
the country!
(whoosh)
Ahh!
All right, now is the
time for us to pull out
all the stops
and show Shishio
that we haven't lost
our fighting spirit
or our will to
survive this battle.
♪
Fine, I'll consider
this the second round
of our final showdown.
♪
Battousai's spirit
is so strong,
that even the leaves
are reacting.
(grunting)
Is Battousai superhuman?
He can't be,
but he's sustained
a burn injury
as well as having
his throat slashed!
How can any normal human being
survive that kind of onslaught,
and still stand up?
One advantage is
that he's half-dead,
and even in his best condition,
he's not as skilled as Shishio.
He could use
his secret principle,
but I doubt he
could carry it off.
So why is it I still feel
incredibly uneasy and afraid?
(growling)
(whimpering)
I'm looking forward to this.
(strong wind)
(yelling)
(sustained yelling)
♪
(gasping)
He's a formidable enemy,
but how does he do it?
Battousai's beyond
human understanding,
and yet I refuse to believe
that Shishio could lose!
Still, there's always
the possibility!
♪
Ahh!
Hmm?
Hey, Kenshin, you're okay!
That's a big relief.
I was really worried about you.
Oh no.
Look at this, my hand
looks like a lost cause.
Ugh...
That'll make it harder.
Kenshin insisted
he wanted to fight
this battle alone,
but I thought
it was a bad idea.
Now, I'm going to have
to rely on him after all.
Shishio!
I'm back!
(leaves snapping)
Well now, what a
pleasant surprise.
Battousai, I do hope
you had a nice trip
to hell and back.
Tell me, are you staying, huh?
Or would you like me
to send you back again?
Well, I certainly hope
that you'll recover
because I'm burning up
with fiery flames
and you're the crazy fool
that's going to feel the heat!
(gasps)
(explosion)
(clank)
He's too tired.
When is it?
(click)
Oh, we've got to stop this.
He's past his 15 minute limit,
and it's dangerous
for him to continue.
Huh?
Think, Hoji,
you've forgotten
Shishio can't sweat
because of all the burns
on his body.
If he doesn't stop now,
his body temperature
will get so high
he'll become
a human bonfire!
You're right,
we have to stop him!
How is that possible
for a human being
to be so very hot?
I can get hotter
than any human.
You see,
when my body
was burned,
my sweat glands
were completely destroyed.
It's impossible to keep
this heat under control.
I can burn just
like a hot flame.
And when I become angry,
the temperature of my body
can become volcanic!
In other words,
the heat's intensity
makes me feel like
I'm burning in hell.
Burning in hell...
Then you must be the devil!
The devil!
(laughs)
I know the doctor
warned Shishio
he could only fight
for 15 minutes at a time.
Who knows what may happen
to him if he's allowed
to continue?
We've got to stop this!
Ahh!
(struggling)
♪
Careful, watch yourself!
I understand now
why Shishio created
the Juppongatana organization
and became its leader.
No one can match
the explosive
power he possesses!
Not even someone
like Battousai!
I don't think
I'll be needing this!
(gasping)
It's useless!
(gasps)
♪
We're supposed to
depend on our leader.
He's strong enough
to defeat them on his own
without our help.
He chose us as his followers,
and it's our duty
to trust our master!
(grunting)
Ha ha!
A steam locomotive
moves by using heat
generated from burning coals.
The hotter the engine gets,
the more forceful it runs.
Shishio's strength
has something to do
with his abnormal body heat.
In theory,
he'll become more powerful as
his body temperature increases.
What if he can't handle
all that strain physically?
Shishio's physical condition
isn't the only
manner of concern.
I'm worried whether or not
Battousai can conquer the heat!
(whoosh)
Whoa-ah!
He got burned!
Huh?
Hmm?
Oh!
(gasp)
(whoosh)
(grunting)
Before you can tap
into the center
of your power,
you must experience pain.
And I'm willing to help
you achieve that goal.
Would you like to be sent
back to the land of the dead?
I'm more than willing
to accomplish that
for a friend like you.
First, you must suffer.
(grunting)
♪
(water rushing)
(gasp)
Kenshin, please,
I don't want you to go.
I have no other choice, Kori.
(quietly sobbing)
But why, why does it
have to be this way?
It's not fair, we just
got to know each other,
and now you might not come back!
I'm not much good at
expressing my feelings,
but the truth is, I love you.
I know, I love you too.
(gasp)
Don't worry, Kori,
nothing is going
to keep me from
coming back to you.
You give me a reason
to go on living.
I'm really going
to miss you, Kenshin.
♪
(quietly weeping)
(loudly sobbing)
♪
Kenshin!
(grunting)
♪
Oh!
Shishio!
Yah!
Shishio has to win.
I'm going to have
to trust his judgment
no matter what technique
Battousai decides to use.
He's a far more
superior fighter.
He's not going to fail me,
I know he won't!
Kill him already!
Your days are numbered.
Take...
...this!
Amazing!
Kenshin, get him
before he gets you!
He's holding his own!
(yelling)
♪
Six five!
You better watch out!
♪
Ugh!
What are you waiting for,
let's continue!
That's incredible,
Shishio appears to be
fully recovered after taking
five blows in a row!
♪
His body's on fire!
(gasps)
Didn't work!
I'm surprised,
I thought Shishio
would incinerate Battousai.
As long as my mind and body
are in a state of readiness,
I can tolerate any pain.
I fought for many years
to get myself to that point.
But I'm not going
to allow you
to inflict pain on others
or trying to live their lives,
it's not going to happen!
I won't allow you
to destroy everything,
because I know what you're doing
is wrong!
I'll rid the world of you!
Hiten Mitsurugi!
Nine-headed dragon, fly!
(grunting)
(gasp)
Ugh.
(panting)
Battousai is holding on
by a thread.
Every blow he receives
brings him closer and closer
towards death,
but somehow
he's resisted the flaming power
that rages within Shishio!
It seems impossible, but true!
And his commitment
to his cause
has given him the advantage,
at least temporarily.
Shishio was taken by surprise
and took a fall.
I can see why Shishio
wanted to kill him so badly.
Killing Battousai
would assure him
that he could take over
as leader of Japan,
but that's not what's
possessing him to do it.
No, it's more
profound than that.
The death of Battousai
would be equal
to taking over the country!
Meeting both of these goals
would be the ultimate conquest!
He must do it,
he must kill Battousai!
(gasping)
(whoosh)
What the hell's going on?
There are flames everywhere!
It's burning up
everything in its path!
The fire's a reflection
of Shishio's rage.
It's reacting to him
like the leaves reacted
to Kenshin.
Like Kenshin?
I think that leaves and fire
are very different things.
Are you ready for
the final showdown?
(gasp)
Oh.
You're alive.
Behold, the secret
sword technique
of Kaguzuchi.
(gasping)
(panting)
Kaguzuchi?
It's truly a secret
if Yumi doesn't know about it.
This has to be
Shishio's most powerful
secret technique!
Kenshin will be forced
to use his secret principle
just like he did with Aoshi.
I hope that he'll be able
to counteract this attack.
(clanging)
(whoosh)
♪
Ugh!
(clanging)
This battle is gonna be
his biggest challenge.
♪
(labored panting)
Kenshin's exhausted.
I hope he's able
to pull it off
in his present condition.
It's over.
I would have to say
this is the end for Kenshin.
(panting)
♪
Battousai's time is up.
The outcome of this battle
is hard to predict.
Shishio's time is running out.
I hope he will prevail.
At last,
now we're going
to find out who's
most powerful of all.
I said I was going
to rid the world of you,
and I meant it.
If it takes every breath
that I have,
I'll make sure
that you never
hurt anyone again!
♪
(panting)