(theme music)
♪
(singing in Japanese)
(wind blowing)
And here's my way of saying
thank you for your cooperation.
Perhaps we can arrange
another deal soon.
There's more where
that came from.
Hmm?
And just who are you gentlemen?
You must pay for using
your political influence
to increase your
personal wealth.
The people demand that you die.
We are the Jinpu Tai.
(gasping)
(crying in fear)
Ohh!
♪
Just what's going on?
(grunting)
♪
(groaning)
Wait, please...
can't we...arrange something?
We've arranged your death.
(grunting)
♪
Hi-ya...hut!
This story gives me the creeps.
So, Kaoru, just who
are the Jinpu Tai?
They are a group of assassins
who have reportedly been
attacking big-name politicians
and high government officials.
But all the people this group
has killed were suspected of
taking bribes or being corrupt,
so a lot of people think the
Jinpuutaiare actually friends
of the people and really
defenders of righteousness.
I don't understand how people
can think radicals murdering
people can have any
righteousness at all.
You're right, it's ridiculous.
Kamiya Kasshin Style of Kendo
is the real sword
of what's right.
Yoshi, sometimes you really
know just what to say.
Ha, what do you
always say "sometimes"?
All right, everyone,
I baked us all some
delicious yams in
an underground pit.
So, who's ready for lunch?
-Me!
Don't worry, Kenshin,
you can have one too.
(laughing)
Mmm, I didn't know anything
from underground...
could be...so sweet.
Who would've guessed
that just hot rocks
could make something
taste this good.
And just think we have
more of these in our garden.
You know what, Kenshin?
I get the feeling Kaoru's
a real potato girl
when it comes to how
she feels about you.
Mmm?
Umm...mmm.
That's because she
only has eyes for you.
(laughing)
Huh?
Jeez, what has got you two
laughing so hard anyway?
Sanosuke!
Is Sanosuke here?
Sanosuke, I need help.
This pupil of mine got very ill
and passed out during class.
We need a doctor immediately!
(gasping)
Just calm down, Teacher.
Now, take a deep breath
and tell us what happened.
This boy was sitting in my class
when he started complaining
of stomach pains,
then he got very dizzy.
The next thing I knew
he was out cold
and I remembered
you know a doctor
so I came right away.
I know a Dr. Gensai,
but he's not presently here.
He's gone to Honshu
to buy some rare herbs
and won't be back for days.
I miss him.
Well, I've got to do something.
(footsteps approach)
Excuse me, let's see.
(quavering)
That's strange,
there's no fever.
-Kaoru, let's go.
-Go what?
Go get the futon laid out.
Kenshin, you get
some hot water ready.
Sure, right away.
So, I take it that you--
You are correct.
This lady is a very
bossy, but good doctor.
But a woman doctor?
Nothing personal, but...
I have complete confidence
in her medical skills,
but her personality...
Sanosuke, I really
don't have the time
to hear your opinion right now.
Your bedside manner
could use some work.
Hey, are you going to force me
to separate you two children?
If it were up to me, I'd give
'em both an hour of detention.
Hey, you got a lot
of nerve to say that.
Please, Teacher,
bring him inside.
Of course.
Hey, ow!
♪
Well, thanks to that
medicine I gave him,
he'll be back to
himself in a few hours.
He just needs rest,
lots of water,
and he'll be all right.
Thank you so much
for helping us out.
I'd rather die than
have one of my kids hurt.
To be honest, you're looking
a little pale, Teacher.
What?
Do you feel dizzy?
Or maybe it's just that
you're a little nervous.
Well, you see that's
probably because
I don't eat as many
meals as I should.
I spend my money on
books instead of food.
I see.
Oh, good.
The little boy's
going to be all right.
Well, that's really
good to hear.
That's really good to hear.
So, I understand that
the man that brought the boy
is a schoolteacher.
Yeah, he lives in the same
cheap housing that I do.
I heard a rumor that
he's a former samurai.
I don't know if that's
really the truth
'cause I've never
seen him fight.
Well, Kenshin doesn't fight
either unless he's forced to.
He does odd jobs
and uses all his money
to keep his school going.
He has his own private
academy where he teaches
the poor children
of the neighborhood
to read and write for nothing.
Really?
That sound wonderful.
Hmm?
♪
Just what is it, Kenshin?
I don't know.
It's just for some reason,
this guy looks really familiar.
Oh.
Now I got it.
I know him from
walking Sano home.
(wind whirring)
So, we need
a skilled assassin,
but how come?
As we target more
visible politicians,
their security forces will be
more difficult to overcome.
To assure ourselves success,
we must control the outcome.
We need a strong closer.
This high-pressure position will
require a complete professional.
Our Jinpu Tai Death Squads
are effective, but we need
to upgrade to an
assassin the level
of Battousai the Slasher.
Yes, we need to find
ourselves another Battousai.
Do you think
I'm asking too much, Toma?
I think I know of such a man.
Are you really serious?
If his skills are
as sharp as I remember
he's as good a slasher
as Battousai ever was.
Good, you'll see to it.
Yes, sir.
♪
(grunting)
(rapid footsteps)
♪
So, Kenshin, what are you
cooking for dinner tonight?
Well, since we got such
a good price on these turnips,
I'm planning on woking them up
with some wild greens,
shitakes and adding
a little vegetable broth.
-Hmm?
-Huh?
What just caught your eye?
It's that teacher
that came over yesterday.
(grunting)
Hey!
Why don't you stop
and take a little rest,
like the rest of us are doing?
Yeah, Teacher, you haven't put
that pick down in three hours.
What's up?
Three hours, you're joking.
I'll rest after this
section's finished.
He's dedicated to
whatever he does.
He is remarkable.
♪
Wha...?
(growling)
Looks like he's
gonna be dead meat.
(growling)
(metal clanging)
(grunting)
(gasping)
You are amazing.
Who are you?
My name is Toma Suzuki.
Suzuki, be sure not
to ever try that again.
Your sword skills
are still sharp,
but I must say I'm insulted
you don't remember me.
I have forgotten my old life.
Well, we're going to see
each other again soon.
Good day.
Teacher, you all
right after that?
Why would a guy like
that go attacking you?
What speed!
What was that?
That teacher's sword
thrust was so quick
I couldn't tell
what style it was.
That was a Hino Haiito Style
of a mysterious
sword technique,
Shiden No Tachi.
Shiden No Tachi?
It is a technique preferred
by assassins because it allows
the opponent no time to react
and defend themselves.
It is as swift
as it is deadly.
So, then just what is
that teacher all about?
Years ago, I battled him
and his sword once in a forest.
You did what?
When?
Ten years ago, I was
still terrorizing Edo
and its surrounding
areas as Battousai.
After disposing of three
members of a security patrol
I intercepted
outside the palace,
I had my encounter with him.
A rival slasher named
Heihachirou Sasaki.
♪
His Shiden No Tachi technique
was so fast and fluid
I was thoroughly convinced
he hadn't come close
to touching me, but he had.
And we left respecting
each other's ability.
He was highly feared
in the Tokugawa era.
Even though I saw it
with my own eyes,
it's hard to picture that
teacher as a feared slasher.
Boy, in a million years,
I would never guess
that about him.
I guess you just can't judge
people by how they look.
(dog barking)
(humming)
I was pretty lucky
to win this jug of sake.
I should share the wealth
and go have a drink
with the teacher
on the way home.
Huh.
Someone you know wants
to have a talk with you.
♪
It's the teacher,
but who are they?
♪
Thanks for coming, Mr. Sasaki.
I apologize for
the other day.
All right, Toma,
I know you've got
something else in mind, so,
what really brought you here?
♪
When I began
studying Hino Haiito,
you were already a master.
Though I truly valued
you as a teacher,
I wasn't mature enough
to appreciate your skill.
It's obvious that
you're dedicated
and you've improved
a lot since then.
Why, thank you.
I didn't mean that
as a compliment.
I think of how many people
you must've killed to get
your skills where they are.
The swordsmanship
you showed me earlier
is the style of a
cold-blooded killer.
You helped teach me, Sasaki.
The sword is made
to kill people.
That mighty sword.
How would you like to
possess its power again?
You want me to kill?
The restoration government
has plans to exterminate
people like us,
but they are the ones
that should be eliminated.
They misuse their positions
and create laws that
only benefit them.
We can't let these rats
corrupt our society.
We must do our duty.
You really think
the way to solve things
is to kill everyone?
Things must change,
and this sword will
be the catalyst.
Don't you want to be
a part of the solution
that will save our society?
Don't you want your name
written in the history books?
Are you asking me if I want
my name written in blood
for all mankind to know
me as an assassin?
Murderers should be executed
instead of being famous.
What?
There are more constructive
ways to change society.
I tossed aside
the sword and now,
instead of embracing death,
I embrace life
through my students.
By teaching these kids
I treasure so much,
I can change society in
a much more positive way,
and make up for the killing
I did that was senseless.
♪
I would appreciate it if
you never call on me again.
Wait.
We Jinpu Tai always
get what we want
and you are the same
as we are, Sasaki.
I think you'll soon
see it our way.
It just may take some time
to realize that we're right.
You're wrong.
♪
This guy has got the same
dedication that Kenshin has.
Hmm, I'm impressed, Teach.
♪
(shouting unintelligibly)
Bounce the ball, Susie.
So, what did Sasaki do?
Well, he politely,
but firmly declined,
but those Jinpu Tai guys
looked pretty fierce.
I'm concerned what
they might try next.
Excuse me, Sanosuke.
I was wondering if you might
help us out with the cleaning.
Don't waste your breath,
we're almost done.
San, no...no...go...big...schmo!
I heard that.
-Grandpa!
(laughing)
You're home!
(cheering)
Well, I certainly missed you,
my little angels.
Welcome home from your
journey, Dr. Gensai.
Oh, thanks, I brought
lots of medicines back,
but no matter
how far you travel,
gee, it's good to be
back home again.
So, Grandpa, were
you thinking about us
during all your traveling?
I couldn't think
of anything else.
After all, you two
are my worldly treasure.
By teaching these children
that I treasure so much,
I can really change society.
Through my students, I am
able to embrace my life.
-I have to go.
-What?
Huh?
See you later!
Where's he going
in such a hurry?
Wait, I got it.
He probably figured if he
stayed here, Megumi would
find a way to put him to work.
We, of the Jinpu Tai, will
always get what we want.
-Teacher?
-Huh?
How's this look?
Good, I'd like to
have a closer look.
Would you please bring it here?
Yes, sir.
See?
Huh...mmm!
(grunting)
I'll be right back.
Huh, Toma.
I've decided which official
will be our next target.
What?
Come join us...that way,
your students will live.
Humph.
You wouldn't.
(growling)
(panting)
Sanosuke!
Tikamatsu, what's the matter?
Our teacher was taken away by
a weird-looking military guy.
Damn, well, tell me
which way did they head out?
Towards Shinagawa.
I had a hunch about that,
I knew that creep was gonna
come back to his school.
(grunting)
(horses neighing)
Whoa!
Huh?
Assemblyman Kataro,
get out of the carriage.
We have some bad news for you.
You must pay for
your corrupt ways.
It-it's the Jinpu Tai.
What?
(groaning)
(horse neighing)
♪
(panting)
What happened?
It's the Jinpu Tai.
What was that?
Where are they?
At the outskirts of town.
♪
(quavering)
Mmm hmm.
Mr. Sasaki.
Huh?
You must carry out what
you were meant to do.
For you, there's
no turning back now.
You know this is your destiny.
-Hold it!
-Huh...what?
♪
It's...Sanosuke.
Put down that sword,
you live to nurture life,
not destroy it.
And just who are you?
I am Sanosuke Sagara,
and you Jinpu Tai are
despicable to use innocent
children to force a good man
to do your dirty work.
Now, leave here!
No, they'll hurt the children.
Could you stop that?
Stand up like a real man,
you gutless wimp.
Huh?
You know, right now I don't have
time to protect you, Kataro.
I'm kind of outnumbered here,
so you're on your own.
Run for it!
♪
Come on!
I do admire your courage.
Most men won't challenge us,
even if they do have a weapon.
(panting)
Ha!
(gasping for air)
Who are you?
Kenshin!
Why do you hold your sword
on a man with no weapon?
What is the challenge in that?
Are the Jinpu Tai just bullies
or do they want
a real challenge?
You can't stop them.
A reversed edge
sword, well now.
I accept your challenge,
and please, men,
don't interfere.
Allow us to fight
'til the death.
Your move.
I will!
Hi-yaahhh!
Yah!
♪
(lightning striking)
(gasping)
That was awesome.
(high-pitched whistling)
We must start this match
again when we're positive
we won't be interrupted.
I assure you the next time
we meet in battle,
I will drive my sword
straight through your throat!
Boy, are we glad you came along.
Yeah.
I was glad to help.
That guy uses the same sword
technique as you do, Sasaki.
I trained him.
You did a good job.
Even before you
were a good person,
you were a good teacher.
After all, he did scratch me.
♪
It's hard to imagine
it's been 10 years.
Then, you are him.
I never would've guessed that
you're Battousai the Slasher.
Well, I'm kind of glad
I left that name back in Edo.
I can't exactly say
I'm proud of what I did,
but it would be
so easy to go back.
Back to the violent and
destructive lifestyles
all of us once lived.
But that life
leads to nowhere.
Your hands aren't meant to hold
a sword anymore, Teacher.
Your guiding hands
help now by teaching
children reading and writing.
Thank you, Sanosuke.
You helped me overcome my doubts
and I promise both of you
I will never hold
a sword in my hand again.
That's great news.
Mmm hmm.
He's right,
man has a choice.
He can create for all mankind,
or he can destroy others
and himself in the process.
(theme music)
♪