(theme music)
♪
You're our enemy, Himura!
If I were to
let you live,
then that would mean
death for the rest of us!
You're wrong, I don't
want to kill you.
Stop your lying!
♪
(growling)
(yelling)
♪
Dearest Lord, I beseech
Thee to accept my offering.
The sacrifice of
Kenshin Himura's life
for Your good
and the good
of all Your
Christian people.
♪
How strange.
When you were a slasher,
you killed your fellow man.
That's a mortal sin.
You are evil and
must be killed
to save the rest of us.
You're wrong,
it's been ten years
since I've killed a man,
I don't want to kill anyone,
you're making a
terrible mistake!
You liar!
You live to
serve the devil!
Kaiou has told me.
You're an evil
inhuman killer!
Kaiou?
Himura is evil incarnate,
an inhuman monster trying
to destroy all that is good.
He has been sent here
from hell to kill us all.
(growling)
All that is
evil must die!
♪
(barking)
I tell you,
I am not evil!
Now let me go, I don't
want to kill anyone!
Quiet, liar!
♪
(grunting)
You broke it.
(growling)
♪
Huh?
(whimpering)
No, stop it,
don't attack me!
(shouting)
♪
Now hold on,
we'll try to escape.
Huh?
Quick, grab me.
What do you mean?
(grunting)
♪
(panting)
I don't get it.
How come you helped me?
You are an evil demon.
Why didn't--
I'm not an evil demon.
Like I've been
trying to tell you,
I don't want to kill
or harm anyone.
I'm just glad I could get
us away from those dogs.
Huh?
Wow, looks like you
got a pretty nasty bite
on your arm there, maybe--
(gasping)
Hey, I'm just
trying to help.
We had specially
trained those dogs
so that they would attack
when they heard that whistle.
You broke the whistle so
now we cannot control them.
You doing that is gonna
make Shogo awful mad.
You should've let
the dogs eat me
'cause now I just
don't know what to do.
Don't you see?
Kaiou will kill me.
Why?
You saved my life
so I won't kill you.
I've learned to reward
kindness with kindness.
I'm sorry that
I have to do this,
but please understand.
(clanking)
Please stay here while
I go ask Lady Magdalia
just what I should do.
I'll be back soon!
Hey, wait!
I can't wait here!
(audible sigh)
(barking)
(shouting)
(panting)
♪
(grunting)
(audible sigh)
Huh?
♪
Bark all you want,
you half-brained hounds,
'cause you'll never get me.
You mutts might as well
attack each other!
If I were a dog,
I'd relieve myself
right on your heads,
you big-butted
barking buffoons!
(laughing)
Ah!
Oh no!
♪
(grunting)
Why is that I always wind up
with the really tough jobs?
♪
Agh!
(gulping)
I should've known
this thing was cursed
when I gave it back and that
girl slapped me in the face.
(grunting)
♪
(shouting)
Kori!
Darn it, something
must have happened,
I just know it.
And I was supposed
to protect Kori
while Kenshin was gone.
Huh?
Hey, wait a minute.
That's Santo, the guy
I saw with Governor Elsten.
Huh, why would he be
coming to Shimabara?
Well, he can't be
up to any good.
Mr. Kaiou, I'm very pleased
that you invited us here.
(chuckling)
♪
You must be the one.
You're Shogu Amakusa.
You are correct.
And you must be
Himura's woman.
(gasping)
♪
Please, you must
explain to me
why you want
to kill Kenshin.
Because it is
my fate to do so.
Why is it your fate?
Without question,
Himura's Amakakeru
Ryu no Hirameki
is the ultimate
sword technique
that exists on Earth,
but I have taken
that technique
and raised
it to a level
that is actually
above almighty Heaven.
So this is my fate.
My sword, which
is above Heaven,
must destroy Earth's
dominant sword
so that Hiten Mitsurugi
can be redefined by me.
♪
So you really think you're
better than any other human?
♪
Well, you're wrong!
You're a vain,
pompous man
and if you truly
understood Kenshin,
you'd leave him alone!
I really don't know
if you're a better
swordsman than Kenshin.
Maybe it's absolutely
true what they say.
Maybe you are able to use
your sword like a god.
I don't care
how good you are.
There's no way you'll
beat my Kenshin.
(water trickling)
Because you are bad.
You are nothing but an
evil merchant of death.
You have said you come
in the name of God,
yet you try to
change people's minds
by senseless killing!
(water trickling)
Hmm.
That's your opinion.
But I must say
you're mistaken.
Look to thyself.
Your leaders have
been responsible
for the deaths of thousands
of God-fearing Christians.
I will avenge
an eye for an eye.
It is time
for a baptism.
Uh, baptism?
Once, long ago, God purged
the world of corrupt humans
by flooding the Earth.
He left only a handful
of righteous people
to repopulate
the world.
I will accomplish
the same thing
in this decadent Meiji Era.
I will destroy this
country's corrupt authorities.
This country will be
baptized in the blood
of those evil men,
and I will be the one
to choose who will
rebuild this nation.
And if you're lucky,
you will live to see it!
You are insane if
you truly believe
you have the right to
say who lives or dies.
Kenshin is
nothing like you.
He would never consider
killing anyone
to change things.
He knows that kindness
works much better than
brute force ever will.
He's a man filled with
love and compassion
and you're nothing
but a monster!
♪
(groaning)
You dare you to
compare the child of God
with the son
of a human?
There is no comparison.
(grunting)
Why do you keep
staring at me?
I'll tell you why!
Your being a man of
God is beyond belief!
Your eyes are
telling me
something
completely different.
♪
(audible sigh)
Now the time has come
for you to go tell him.
Tell Himura it's time
for his last fight.
Ah, who are you?
I'm Kori, Kori Kamiya.
Kori Kamiya.
(panting)
Boy, am I glad that
you're both here!
I need your help to
tell me what to do
about that guy back there.
Just who do you mean?
I mean Battousai Himura.
(gasping)
I can't just wait here.
It's been over an hour.
Sano might be in trouble.
But if I don't wait here
for Janoman to return,
then Amakusa
might kill him.
♪
Kenshin!
What are you doing here?
♪
Whoa, how did you
break out of this chain?
You could've just
walked away from here.
Thank you.
You are something.
This is another example of
why you'll never be great.
To achieve greatness,
you must know that your needs
are above everyone else's.
You're just too
stupid to know that.
Huh?
I begin to understand
you, Himura.
You think of
other people first
and you believe by
being kind to people,
you can change
their hearts
and how they think.
(thundering)
Well, I will prove
that your strength
is really just
a weakness.
♪
Since Hiko told me
that you were a master
of Hiten Mitsurugi style,
I knew that a showdown with
you would be inevitable.
But fighting you is
not why I am here.
Defeating you
is not my goal.
I have come here
not to fight,
but, instead, I'm here to
teach you what you need
to know about
human nature.
Hiten Mitsurugi is meant
to protect the people.
Protecting the people is the
real reason it was created
and the only way
to truly use it.
This was not
only the belief
of all the successive
Seijuro Hikos,
but it was also
accepted by Hyouei,
who taught you
Hiten Mitsurugi.
Hiten Mitsurugi
was never used
as an offensive technique,
it is to defend,
not to attack.
Here, I brought
this from Hyouei,
he really wanted
you to have it.
This is his will, he gave
it to me on his deathbed.
Uncle Hyouei?
♪
You must read this
before you fight me.
Wrong, I don't have
to read anything.
You don't seem to understand
that my Hiten Mitsurugi style
is much more advanced
than your pathetic
defensive technique.
I've taken it far beyond
the thought of any human,
including Hyouei.
Try to understand that for
the sword above heaven,
all human thought
is meaningless.
♪
Well, that's a shame.
Since that's
how you feel,
I'll just put Hyouei
here to watch us.
♪
(thundering)
It's about to begin.
This is it.
It's going to happen.
♪
Be sure to
watch carefully.
Shogo's the one-and-only
sword above heaven.
♪
(thundering)
(yelling)
(gasping)
Is that your tornado
thrust technique?
Well, it's my turn.
Time for you
to see what a real
tornado thrust
looks like!
♪
I've never seen
Hiten Mitsurugi
taken to such a level.
His speed is
beyond God Speed,
it's more like
super God Speed.
♪
Twirling Ryunkansen.
Watch out!
Still standing, eh?
I see why they call
you a legend.
You really must be
a legendary swordsman
to withstand
my initial attack.
There's no doubt that Shogo
is the sword of God.
Now I see
what you mean.
-Right.
-Kenshin, get ready!
Even Master Hiko would've
been surprised by that move.
It was amazing to see
that tornado thrust
with a twirl.
Considering your
incredible speed,
I expect your next
technique to be Ryusosen.
Hmm?
But I don't
think my knowing
what your next move
is will stop you.
You're right, it won't.
But I want to see
your Ryusosen as well.
♪
Let's do it.
Here I am.
(grunting)
Kenshin!
(groaning)
♪
(whimpering)
(grunting)
I know he's badly hurt,
but his concentration won't
allow him to give up now.
♪
It's amazing that
you're able to control
the power that
you possess.
I'm sure that if you
had really wanted to,
you could've finished
me off already.
You could've cut off
my left arm completely
if you had wanted.
Yes, but that wouldn't
have served my purpose.
It would be meaningless
to have you die now.
I want you to show me
the ultimate
swordsmanship on Earth.
♪
So you're going
to use Kuzuryusen.
Oh, Kenshin.
It looks as though
you're right.
I guess Shogo wants to
see Kenshin try to counter
with his Amakakeru
Ryu no Hirameki.
♪
With his strength diminished,
he can't use any
other counter technique
and Shogo knows it.
This should be most
excellent, Himura.
You have no
other move left
but your Amakakeru Ryu
no Hirameki death blow.
Good luck.
♪
Time you saw the
sword from Heaven.
♪
Kuzuryusen.
Get ready!
(yelling)
♪
I can't believe it.
It didn't look like Amakusa
delivered a killer blow.
Why not?
(yelling)
(gasping)
Unbelievable.
Kenshin countered
Amakusa's Kuzuryusen
with his own Kuzuryusen.
♪
I'm shocked.
I thought I left
you no other move
but your Amakakeru
Ryu no Hirameki.
Why didn't you use that
to defend yourself?
Because I had to show you
that the people of Earth
sometimes lead
with their hearts.
Huh?
You cannot break the
human spirit, Shogo.
What?
(grunting)
(thundering)
Now I will
give you a loss
that is even
worse than death!
♪
(thundering)
(gasping)
♪
Eternal darkness!
Kenshin, oh, no!
(panting)
(waves crashing)
He's gone!
(sobbing)
♪
(audible sigh)
(gasping)
No!
Oh, Kenshin!
Kenshin!
(sobbing)
♪
Are you all right?
Kori?
(gasps)
I'm sorry I
made you worry.
I hope I haven't
caused you pain.
Kenshin, I don't want
you to talk that way,
you're going
to be all right!
Oh, I love you, Kenshin.
I love you so much.
You're gonna
be all right!
It's you, Yoshi.
It's really good
to hear your voice.
I'm glad you're both safe.
Huh?
I'll give you a loss
that is even worse than
death itself, Kenshin.
Eternal darkness.
(whooshing)
And Amakusa attacked
me with Rairyusen
and since then,
my eyes completely lost
their power
to see forever.
What is it?
Huh, Kenshin?
Oh no!
He can't see!
(theme music)
♪