♪
The instructions for finding
the medicine are clear.
Follow the hand of
the Goddess of Mercy.
She will point you to a path
that is very dark
and treacherous.
If you're not careful,
you'll fall into the abyss.
(screaming)
♪
(rumbling)
That's convenient.
You Japanese think of
everything, don't you?
Enough small talk!
Jump if you dare!
♪
I'm impressed!
This temple is
absolutely astounding!
The design's reminiscent of
something from Greek mythology!
I bet some almond-eyed cheat
copied it right out
from under them.
♪
What's this?
How odd.
This isn't time to play
with rocks, Schneider.
This isn't a rock, Lentz!
As a matter of fact,
it's petrified wood.
This entire building
was made out of wood
a very long time ago.
Hmm.
The architecture
doesn't look Japanese.
Although it has
similar features,
it's somewhat foreign to me.
Do you have any idea
who might've built this
structure, Misanagi?
The ancient Suwa built this
temple thousands of years ago
before they were taken over
by the Yamato civilization.
The Suwa people
developed the medicine,
and have concealed the
formula all these years.
We are their direct descendants.
Ah, I see what you're up to.
You want Japan in
exchange for the formula
because you're related
to some dried-up ancestors.
Pretty lofty ambition for
a monkey like you, I'd say.
Remove your filthy paws before
I crush you like an insect.
Tramp!
♪
Misanagi, who are those bats?
They are my
personal body guards.
Around here, they're
called "the Sanada Three."
Uh, that sounds intriguing.
We better find out if
they're as good as they sound.
Stop it, Lentz!
We aren't here to
make any trouble,
so behave like a gentleman!
I'm sure she has no
intention of harming us.
I want you to treat her
with the respect she deserves.
I'm sorry.
My father's motto was
"courage, respect, and honor."
There's no boundary when it
comes to treating a female
with utmost courtesy.
You made you point.
Let's get a move on, shall we?
-After you.
-Hmm?
The tradition in my country
is to put women on a pedestal
and make sure they're given
all the courtesies
that they are due.
Please, be so kind.
I'm impressed.
(grunting)
Huh?
Misao, are you all right?
Kori, wake up.
Speak to me, please!
I have a headache.
What is that smell?
What happened to us?
How did we get into
this horrible place?
I don't know, but if we
don't get out of here fast,
we're gonna suffer the same
fate as these people did.
Well, what do you mean by that?
Have you seen any dead bodies?
What if we can't
get out of here?
I'm much too young to die,
and I really hate
being in the dark!
Kenshin, you've
gotta do something!
I had no idea that
the Black Knights
were collaborating
with the Sanada Ninjas.
You know what?
This is all your fault, Yutaro!
Quit complaining!
All you ever do is--
(indistinct fighting)
You're just a puny
hothead with an attitude!
Just who are you
calling a hothead?
You're a catastrophe
waiting to happen!
(grunting)
Hey you two, would you mind
taking this someplace else?
If I wanted a good massage,
I'd find myself a geisha!
This is a bad time to fight.
At least the fall didn't
affect their spirit!
So tell me something, Kenshin.
Where are we going from here?
It's important we
get to that medicine
before those Black Knights do.
This place is so hot, I'm
sweating just like a pig!
And it's startin'
to stink in here!
It is pretty bad.
Problem is it's so dark in here.
How will we ever
find our way out?
Excuse me, hello?
Don't you guys realize
you're in the company
of a genuine ninja warrior?
I'm used to working in the dark!
It's not a problem for me,
so let me shed a bit
of light on the subject.
Whoa, it's a good thing
you came along after all!
You saved us!
Hold it!
Don't you dare light that match!
That smell is sulfur, and
if there are any dead bodies,
it could produce a deadly blast!
A chemical reaction
sometimes occurs
when sulfur is combined with
gases from a decomposing corpse.
The place'll blow up if
there's any type of spark.
Whoa!
If the volcano remains
inactive, we're relatively safe,
but you never can tell
about those things.
Huh?
Unfortunately, we don't
have time to run any tests.
We better find a way out of here
before the whole
darn thing explodes.
You know, Yutaro, you may
have a point about that.
We'll be stir-fried
if we don't find a way
to climb out of
this hellhole fast!
Come on, let's think.
The gas is starting
to build up--look!
If we breathe too much of
this gas, it could kill us!
It's getting thicker!
Now it's really
starting to stink!
(groaning)
The path is blocked and
there's no way to climb out!
She's right, there's
nowhere else we can go!
Oh, no!
If we don't get out of here,
we'll all end up dead meat!
It's getting really
hard to breathe!
We're gonna suffocate!
Somehow we've gotta break
through that stone wall!
Hey, Sano, your fist is
our only hope right now!
If I thought I could
break through it, I would,
but that wall's much
too thick for me.
But it's our only chance.
I gotta give it a try!
Hurry, before I choke!
Come on, Sano, if
you don't do it soon,
I'm going to pass out!
What?
Hey, what's that sound?
Huh?
We hit the jackpot!
It's a spring!
This is incredible.
Now we don't have to
worry about suffocating!
This water must be
coming from underground!
That means that there
are water channels
on the other side of this wall
so we could swim out!
If we can find a safe
way to get into the flow,
we can get out of here!
We gotta break
through that wall!
Sano, try your
rock-breaking punch!
You've got it!
As long as it gets us
out of this horrible mess.
(yelling)
(rumbling)
What's this place?
I'm not really sure.
This is the first occasion
I've had to come here.
Huh?
What's that?
♪
Well, this can't be!
Let me see.
Just take a peek at this crest.
It's almost like mine, see?
That's quite an
unusual coincidence.
There are some differences,
but the basic design
is very similar.
This crest belongs
to the Sanada Ninjas.
And no one else should know
about it except our group.
It's probably
just some dumb luck.
He could be right.
Look, there may be other
similarities we're not aware of.
Yes, sir.
There's some writing!
The engraving is worn down,
and it's hard to read.
From what I can see,
the formation of the letters
appears to be Western
rather than Japanese script.
Meldars, look!
Huh?
There's another one of
those sign posts over there!
What do you think
this could mean?
I don't know, but I've seen them
in practically every
junction we've passed.
Some kind of road sign.
Come on, let's go.
♪
Something wrong?
Um, nothing.
I was just remembering something
I had read in my country
that could offer an
explanation for all of this.
What's that?
Well, rumor has it that
several of my ancestors
came to Japan as seamen
thousands of years ago,
so it's possible this
legend could be true.
These sign posts
could be living proof
that our two groups
are both connected.
It's possible we've
come together now
because we're fulfilling
our ultimate destiny.
Hmm, that seems a little
far-fetched, don't you think?
I find you amusing.
Others have told me that.
We have to get going
before the sun comes up.
♪
(coughing)
I swallowed too much water!
You people are pathetic.
Couldn't you have thought
of a more efficient
way to get here?
Hey, we're lucky we made it out!
Not everybody's a ninja
supergirl like you are,
so have some patience
with us regular people.
Kenshin, there's someone
lying on the ground!
He looks hurt!
We're coming!
Stay right there!
No, really, I'll be fine,
I'll just stay here
and drown, thanks.
Hurry up!
He looks hurt pretty badly!
He's dressed like a ninja!
You're right, Kori!
He's the guy who attacked
us when we were in Suwa!
How is he doing?
He's barely alive.
He took a really bad fall.
We can't just leave him
here alone like this.
Leave me alone.
You have to stay
right where you are
or you might injure
yourself even more!
Oh, yeah?
I'm a ninja, and I'm not
going to die like this!
So just step back, all of you!
No way!
Wait, Misao.
Huh?
I don't understand it.
This fella belongs to the
Sanada Ninja group, doesn't he?
How come they left
him alone here to die?
Shut up, it's none
of your business!
Don't cause any trouble!
Or I'll make sure to take
you with me as a souvenir
when I'm dead!
All that really
matters right now
is you getting
back in good health.
After that's done, we'll
talk about your problem.
I'm fine.
If you promise to attack, I--
(grunting)
He's lost consciousness again.
Good, he's safer that way.
This is bad.
We have to operate
on him right away!
Huh?
Uh, operate?
He'll die if I don't try!
You gotta help me save
this guy's life, please!
Yutaro!
He's right.
I don't know what I'm doing,
but I'll do my best to help you.
This is my grooming kit.
Can you use it?
The razor could
work as a scalpel.
And I see you have a needle
and thread--perfect.
The hot water's all ready!
Let's see if we can
find a concave rock
to pour all the water into!
Ow, okay!
♪
Look at that steam come up!
How come you have to boil
all that stuff, anyway?
Yeah, it looks like
a big old pain to me!
To kill the germs.
You see, if the
wound becomes dirty,
it could get infected,
and that would
make it a lot worse.
You can't put your
hands in there!
Yeah, don't be stupid!
You'll burn 'em up!
(grunting)
Yutaro!
You better get your hands
out of there right now!
No, not yet!
What--why not?
It's important, Yoshi.
I have to do it for
the patient's sake.
Listen, you dummy,
the patient's our enemy!
But every person deserves
the right to be treated!
It doesn't matter
if he's an enemy,
a doctor is bound
to save as many sick
and injured people as possible!
If I'm going to become a doctor,
I have to abide by the creed.
It's the ethical thing to do!
♪
(grunting)
Is he gonna make it?
Well, I closed up the wound.
All we can do now
is hope for the best.
He appears to be stabilizing,
as far as I can see.
All his vital signs are normal.
I'm very impressed with the
skill you showed us, Yutaro.
And I even learned something
about Western-style medicine!
Thank you, Kori,
but if you don't mind,
I think we oughta get going.
Hmm?
Well, we have to go back
and find that medicine!
If the Black Knights get
a hold of that formula,
it'll be a disaster!
But Yutaro!
They're already
so far ahead of us!
I realized after I
performed the operation.
It's important we
find the medicine
so no one has to suffer anymore.
The Black Knights can't
keep the secret formula
exclusively to themselves.
I agree with you.
You can't get up!
You'll pull out your stitches!
There's no time
to worry about that.
Take me with you, please.
I can help to show you the way.
You'd do that?
My name is Kaita, I'm a ninja,
but now, I'm exiled from Sanada
because I had a
disagreement with our leader.
I wouldn't trust him.
He might be trying to trap us.
He wants us to believe
that he's on our side,
and then he'll turn
around and kill all of us!
I know that you don't
trust me, but you have to!
If you don't the Black Knights
will get away with murder!
Take me!
I'm telling you all the truth!
♪
Go through here,
and you'll come out
in the exact same spot
that you originally fell.
Then we'll proceed from there.
You hurt?
Don't worry, it's all right now.
Let's hurry up and go inside.
We don't have a
lot of time left.
Think we should?
I think we should.
I don't know, what would make
him change his mind about this?
I can't say, but we're just
gonna have to trust him for now.
Hey, could be that his
conscience got to him,
and he wants to live the
straight and narrow path.
Are you sure about that?
He's the most naive
man I've ever met.
Well, I guess I'd
better back him up.
Well, I hope he's right.
Hmm?
(grunting)
Close call.
That's deep.
Looks like a stairway to hell.
Go ahead, I'll catch up
with you when it's safe.
Mhm.
I'll go first, then
one person at a time,
and don't make any noise.
♪
Hey, I found another
road marker!
Hmm.
(bats squeaking)
♪
What?
The red-headed swordsman's
group is coming down?
Ren, Jin, find Baku and
attack them when they get here.
Misanagi, why are you
speaking to those bats?
Because emissaries of the ninjas
don't necessarily have
to exist in human form.
I knew you ninjas were batty.
That figures.
Leave it to the Orientals
to use beasts as servants.
What a joke!
What's that?
Get away from me!
(grunting)
Baku's bats have
a very bad temper.
Don't get them mad or you're
going to be very sorry.
We didn't mean to offend you.
All right, he's had enough.
Get out of here.
I shouldn't have
said what I said.
I hope you forgive me!
(laughing)
Hmm?
I have to say, this isn't
quite as bad as I thought.
Well, that's odd.
Those bats have never
been friendly with anyone
except Baku and myself.
That's really weird.
Well, maybe I better rethink
my profession and be a ninja!
Ha, I'm not sure about that.
Ninja training is
extremely brutal work.
Maybe you could make it
easier for me, huh?
-Misanagi?
-Huh?
I believe you
mentioned something
about the red-headed swordsman.
That's right.
Apparently he's back
with his group intact.
And to top it off, Kaita is
the one who's been guiding them
all the way down here.
Impossible!
Yeah, he's right.
I personally got
rid of him for good!
He must've come
back from the dead!
I don't know how they lived
through that fall
into the abyss,
but somehow they survived.
The bats have told me that Kaita
is leading them down our
secret path to get here.
I see.
We'll have to take care of 'em.
Well, I--this ought
to be interesting.
More men.
We better take them out first
so we can get to the others.
Kenshin!
I'll do it, just
give me a chance!
You dummy!
Those guys are
ninjas, not amateurs!
You can't expect your
wooden sword technique
to get rid of them!
Get lost before you get hurt!
But Sano, remember what
you told me yourself!
If Yutaro can become a
physician to help people,
then why can't I use
my stick the same way?
Can I see if it works?
This isn't the time or the
place to experiment with that!
Sano,
Yoshi's impressed with Yutaro's
performance as a doctor,
so we should give
him his chance.
Yoshi, this is going
to be dangerous,
but if you really wanna do it,
we'll be right here
to back you up, 'kay?
Mhm.
Hey there!
What do you think
you're looking at,
you big old dummy?
Hey, that's a kid!
You're right, and
he's still alive!
I'm not just a kid!
I'm Yoshi from the
Kamiya Kasshin school,
and I'm your worst nightmare.
What's the matter, guys?
Are you too afraid to fight me?
If you don't quit mouthin' off,
I'll cut your tongue out!
(grunting)
Yoshi!
(yelling)
Great.
Let's get outta here.
Yoshi, are you all right?
Hey, can you stand up?
That was a pretty
good performance.
Oh, yeah?
Don't make fun of me,
you needle-nosed nerd.
I'm not making fun of you!
I thought you did
a really wonderful job!
Hmm?
-Are we friends?
-Yeah.
That's so sweet it
makes me wanna puke!
We better keep going.
♪
Wow, this is incredible!
It's just like a dream world
right in the middle of Japan!
Yeah, it sure is.
Is this the rune in the legend?
I wonder.
Ahh!
Hey, watch out!
(yelling)
Who's the maniac that tried
to plunge a fork in my foot?
Is this some new technique?
♪
Great, we've got some real
lunatics on our hands now.
You are making our
mistress very mad.
Prepare yourselves to die.
Don't let your guard down, guys.
I don't think you
need to tell me that.
Hey, let me at
those weird freaks!
Stay here!
Why should I?
Those men are special
body guards for Misanagi,
the Ninjas' leader.
Jin is known as the headhunter
and Ren is the giant snake.
They are part of
the Sanada Three.
I may be beautiful, but I can
take these guys on anytime.
Huh?
(bats squeaking)
What are all these
bats doing here?
Baku!
The Darkness Wrangler!
I knew he was hiding
here somewhere!
He's the third member
of the Sanada Three.
We'll start with one and
crush 'em one after the other.
♪
I'd like to go one-on-one
with a samurai some day.
Maybe soon.
Schneider, I don't think you'd
wanna fight with this one.
He's the best of them all.
In fact, he's legendary.
He's called "Battousai."
I've heard several
accounts of him.
He must really be incredible!
The pure challenge of it
makes me want to
fight him even more.
I'm afraid that's
very unlikely to happen.
My bodyguards have
been watching him,
and I'd say they've
killed him by now,
so you're probably out of luck.
Oh well, that's too bad.
Schneider, what are you doing?
Come quickly!
You're wasting too much time!
Forgive me, Meldars.
Let's go.
Hmm, of course anyone that
could be defeated that easily
wouldn't be worth
fighting against anyway.
He's lucky he didn't fight me.
Oh no!
They're going wild!
Careful, they're
blood-sucking bats!
Shoo, shoo!
These things are disgusting!
(grunting)
♪
Get off me!
What's the matter with you?
Sanosuke!
All right, I've had enough
of this stupid fork already.
Now you're getting me mad!
(yelling)
♪
He really seems to have
mastered using that whip.
I've never had to deal with
anything quite like this.
It's impossible to figure out
what he's gonna do with it next.
I have to keep my composure,
like a cat
hunting for a mouse.
Since I can't get near him,
there's only one
thing left to do.
♪
(yelling)
(gasping)
♪
My Dor Ryu Sen didn't work!
What now?
♪