(theme song)
♪
(shouting)
(grunting)
♪
(chanting)
Oh...
♪
(soft grunting)
Kori, I'm back now.
If you can hear me,
just nod your head.
♪
Oh, Kenshin.
Good, you're awake!
Easy, you'll need
to rest for a week.
Drink that water.
Sip some of it
three times a day.
Mm.
♪
What are you going to do now?
I was hoping to get some sleep.
Jinpu and I will leave
for Nikko later tonight.
Luckily, it will
take a few days
before the Ryu
Myaku reaches Nikko.
We'll get there ahead of it
and find some way to
rearrange its energy patterns
so that we can direct
the Ryu Myaku away from Tokyo
and destroy it at the same time.
Well, how can we do that, Jinpu?
I mean, this is a mammoth
flow of destructive energy.
What's gonna be strong
enough to stop it?
I don't know.
Well, you'd better know!
Hey Jinpu, this is your
line of work, isn't it?
You're the expert,
don't you have a plan?
It's not something
you can plan ahead.
I must see what
the enemy does first.
Then I will be ready
to formulate my approach.
Why didn't you say
that in the first place?
Hey Sano, I have
a job for you.
It'll take both you
and Tsunan to handle it.
Trying to stop the energy again?
I'll do my best,
that's all I can promise.
Well, don't worry.
I'm not asking that.
Jinpu has got to figure
out exactly where in Nikko
the Ryu Myaku will
change its direction.
He can calculate it if he
has two pieces of information.
I want you guys to
find out why and where
it's supposed to be
hitting in Tokyo.
Think you'll be able
to find that out for us?
That's no problem.
How about you?
Fine.
♪
Where will we meet you?
When we get to Nikko,
we won't be hard to find.
They'll try to stop us.
Just listen for
the sound of fighting.
We'll be there.
♪
I'll go pack
my gear for the trip.
Mm-hm.
♪
I want to help.
Let me go with you.
Water, please!
Mm?
A little water.
Yoshi, listen.
We can't leave Kori
all alone right now.
I want you to look after her.
Oh...
Water, please.
Could I have some water?
I'd better stay.
I'm gettin' your water, Kori!
Be right back.
♪
Mm...
I wish I could help.
Please be careful, huh?
♪
Is that wound on your
foot still bothering you?
I've put the spring water on it.
It should be fine.
We've got a ways to go.
Hope it heals quickly.
Do you have any idea
where Reisui and his gang
might have gone in Nikko to cast
their Tang shui spells from?
I would say Toshogu's
where they might be.
Toshogu is the location
of Ieyasu's mausoleum.
I've been told its ki
is very powerful.
I heard...
What?
A story has been passed on
from one generation to another.
Ah, Ieyasu has supposedly left
behind a gold heralding device
which was hidden
somewhere in Toshogu.
Exactly what does
this device do, Jinpu?
Originally, it was used
to call forth the spirits
that inhabit the earth,
but they say it's so powerful
it can manipulate
all energy freely,
no matter how strong
the energy may be.
Ieyasu Tokugawa was
a member of the wind family,
and only family members
know of the device.
If the story is true,
we may have a way
of stopping Reisui's evil power.
And even though the
Tokugawa Era has ended,
we are still dealing with
animosities set in motion
many years ago.
Mm?
(loud bang)
(grunting)
Quick, Captain,
let's get out of here!
(gasping)
Excuse me, General Yamagata?
Yes?
What do you want?
I've been sent here
on official business.
The cabinet has decided
to relieve you of your duty
in this matter, sir.
(grunting)
What?
How can you even
suggest such a thing
at a time like this?
And you must comply immediately.
This is an order.
You sent the Imperial Army
to Musashino last week
and a private
construction facility
managed by the cabinet
was shut down on your orders
without our consent.
I will now escort you
to your home, General.
You darn fools!
At ease, Captain.
I'm at fault.
You'll be in charge now.
I'll take care of
everything, General.
Now, pack your gear!
We're movin' out.
And burn everything.
I don't want any
evidence left behind.
Let's go.
(maniacal laughter)
Since Reisui is in Nikko
summoning up
the fire dragon spirit,
I think we should go help him
now that we're finished here.
It's not your job to think.
I'm giving the orders.
You just obey me.
(panting)
Hey you!
Stop right there.
(grunting)
Stop, please leave me alone.
Say, listen, we just want
to ask you a few questions.
Look, I already told
the police everything I know.
I'm just a simple office worker.
(trembling)
Well, listen, maybe
something slipped your mind,
am I right?
Yup.
Three months ago,
my boss, Mr. Saeki,
gave me a weird order
which I had forgotten
all about until now.
(snickers)
What was weird about it?
Well, he asked me to make a trip
to every single shrine
from the Senate House
on up into the Northeast
Domain just past Tokyo.
Was there anything
about these shrines
he wanted you to check?
I had to count the number
of southwest gates, that's all.
The police didn't ask,
so I never told them.
That's all I can remember.
I've told you everything,
I'm quite sure about that.
There's nothing else.
Hm.
Hey, I think you're holdin'
somethin' back from us.
No, that's all!
(trembling)
Except one more thing.
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
He asked me to
talk to the Senate.
I was to get a copy
of the decree,
an order to separate
Buddhism and Shintoism.
I made an under the table
deal I can't discuss.
(gasps)
I wonder why that was
so important to Saeki.
I want a copy of that mandate.
I may have an extra
one I can give you.
I like you.
(shrieks)
♪
White, fire, blue, sea.
I will control thee.
Heat, light, burn bright.
Strong wind, come now.
(maniacal laughter)
-It's them!
-Right.
(commotion)
(grunting)
I'm sorry, Commander Kawaji.
I have strict orders.
Not even you are allowed
to go beyond this point.
I must insist you
release General Yamagata
from his house
arrest immediately,
do you understand me, sir?
Mm-mm-mm.
How rude.
What are you cabinet
members thinking?
This is a real emergency.
Can't you see that?
I see you wasting time.
Have you and your staff
prepared security measures
for the important
meeting tomorrow?
What meeting?
The one at the Senate House.
The meeting's scheduled
for 1 p.m. sharp.
Dignitaries and officials
from all over Japan
will be attending
this momentous occasion.
I suggest you focus
your attention on that.
I'll be ready.
Chief, let's go.
Right.
Round up all your men.
We have to secure the entire
area within Tokyo proper,
and I want you to arrest
anyone who looks suspicious.
-Right.
-Move!
I'm on it, sir.
Commander Kawaji.
Can you spare us a moment?
Oh, you two.
What's up?
We don't know yet,
but we persuaded
Saeki's business
manager to tell us
what he didn't tell the police.
He's been checking out
all the shrines near the Senate.
Actually, he found out
something very interesting.
There's a link
between the Ryu Myaku
and all the southwest gates.
When the Ryu Myaku
passes through these gates,
its power increases.
I think Saeki is planning
to throw all that bad energy
at one nearby
target, the Senate.
Huh, what?
There's an important
meeting there tomorrow at 1!
♪
It looks peaceful here.
Yes, there's no sign of any
energy tricks from Reisui.
♪
We need to go around back
because that's where
Ieyasu's grave is located.
♪
In order for Reisui to
activate the flow of the ki,
he needs the energy protection
created by the giant scale
on Ieyasu's tomb.
It's the fifth tip
of the ki star,
but there's no indication
he's even been here.
♪
Hm.
Nothing.
The energy here
doesn't feel evil,
and there's no sign of
any of Reisui's influence.
Hey, Jinpu?
We should look for
the gold heralding device first.
If we have it,
we'll be able to deal
with all of Reisui's tricks,
because it has the power
to change bad ki into good,
isn't that right?
Mm-hm.
Well, I think we should
be leaving for Nikko
as soon as possible.
We'll talk to the man who did
research for the decree first.
He may shed some light
on a lot of things.
This is the place.
Excuse me, sir!
Yes, can I help you?
I'm sorry to barge in on you.
My name is Tsunan Tsukioka.
I publish a newspaper
and I'd really like to ask you
just a few questions about this.
Oh?
Where'd you get this material,
if I may ask?
As a newspaperman,
I make it a rule
to never reveal my sources,
but let me assure you
I won't tell anyone
of our conversation either
if you can explain to me
the meaning of these diagrams
on those pages.
The name of the person
who wrote this
appears at the end
of the document.
Tell me if that name is yours.
Well, is it?
I'm kind of in a hurry here.
Yes, that's me.
It'll take a while to remember.
It better not.
We don't have time to spare!
Take it easy, I'm old.
I'll never forget this.
It's a map of where
Toshogu's ki was removed.
Hm?
The Meiji government feared
the very existence of Toshogu.
They thought as long as Ieyasu
Tokugawa's tomb was there,
the ghost of Tokugawa Era
might rise up from the grave
and take over again.
So certain powerful
officials secretly removed
points of the highest energy
and took them to
a different location.
One item they
transferred out of Toshogu
has the might to manipulate
all energy that exists
in the ground.
This amazing tool belonged
to the wind families.
The officials that took it
never wanted the winds
to find it again.
I remember overhearing
them say just how difficult
the big thing was to bury.
They buried it?
Do you know where?
It was in Senjogahara.
But what is it?
Mm, I was never really
able to find that out.
But I do know if you
make a mistake with it,
it could destroy us.
(gasps)
Furthermore, it requires
something called
a gold heralding device
to empower it.
The government placed
it in the roof facade
of the Yome Gate.
That's such a visible location.
I wonder why they put it there.
Didn't you think it was
inappropriate for that place
to have such
an elaborate facade,
since it's dedicated to Ieyasu,
who counted every penny?
They deliberately
fabricated that facade
so they could
camouflage the device.
Mm-hm.
♪
Fill Kenshin in on
what we already know.
Right.
Ya!
♪
We still haven't found out
why they're doing this.
Right, we need
to do more research.
Where from?
I'm not sure, but this
might give us a clue.
♪
Here we are.
The Yome Gate is
the only place left to search.
Jinpu, take a look over there!
That's a whole row
of heralding devices,
but check out the
one in the center.
It's shiny and new.
I thought they were
supposed to be old.
Uh huh.
What's happened to Usui?
He's supposed to be here.
I don't know, but those
guys Kenshin and Jinpu
were spotted at Toshogu.
How stupid.
There is no way they can stop
the Ryu Myaku from moving.
(laughing)
It's fun time.
I am going to give them
a spellbinding course
in Tang shui.
I doubt very much
they'll be calling on me
to Tang shui their homes
if they live
through this ordeal.
(chanting)
♪
What is that?
What's goin' on?
(exclaiming)
It's Tang shui.
We're stuck here.
How do we make it go away?
♪
This must be Reisui's sorcery.
Huh?
(grunting)
♪
(growling)
Kenshin, listen, don't
breathe his air, understand?
It's poisonous.
I'll only be able to
decrease its strength.
This'll take all your willpower.
Now don't you give up!
You need to just hang in there.
You can't win by fighting it,
you must go with the flow.
(speaking foreign language)
Jack, set.
(growling)
What do I do?
It's locked onto
my every thought.
(laughing)
(grunting)
♪
(growling)
(speaking foreign language)
Jack, set.
(growling)
♪
(speaking foreign language)
Jack, set, go.
♪
Huh?
Set, go!
I mustn't fear it.
I need to find the
right way to beat it.
I've faced many challenges
before in the past.
Maybe it's my own past
I'm fighting to forget.
♪
(growling)
This thing is me.
I've been fighting
with my own dark forces.
I guess Tang shui works
by magnifying the bad energy
in everyone and
turning it against them.
From now on, I've gotta
focus on the forces of light!
(growling)
(grunting)
♪
He broke the spell.
What should we do now, boss?
(snickering)
Nothing to be concerned with.
It's not that important.
All that matters is that
everything goes well tomorrow.
(chanting)
I'd say it looks
like you won, Kenshin.
I hope you got rid of your
phantom once and for all.
Thank you for all of your help.
Your knowledge of feng shui
proved invaluable, Jinpu.
Almost...
there.
Just what I thought,
it's a fake.
I'll bet the real
gold heralding device
was stolen years ago.
Sano!
Kenshin!
We got some big problems
that we need to take
care of right away.
The Senate's
his probable target,
but there is something
that can be used to stop him.
We gotta find it fast.
It's some gold heralding device.
Huh?
I can't figure it out.
It's like a puzzle.
Besides, I'm too tired.
It's interesting.
I'm really starting
to see something here.
What?
An energy field being
set up around Kyoto,
our former capital.
Somebody wants to bring
the ki back to the way it was
in the Tokugawa Era.
What do you mean?
All right, look at this.
Kyoto is here,
and Edo castle is here.
The starting point for
the energy flow is at Uno,
here in the northeast.
This area was once
protected by shrines
with spiritual power
equal to Toshogu.
You follow me?
Which was the main shrine?
Probably this one.
It was originally built by
the same guy who built Toshogu,
Ieyasu's resting place.
But it was rebuilt to be
more like the one in Kyoto,
which is a demon gate.
Kanaji?
It burned down in the middle
of the war six years ago.
I wonder if they
burned it down on purpose
so they could turn it
into a gate for demons.
I want to know right now
who ordered it rebuilt and why.
(grunting)
I'm too tired to tackle
that question tonight.
It bothers me that scars
from the Tokugawa Era
are affecting us this much.
No, you can't talk
to Commander Kawaji.
He's busy.
Who's out there?
It's me.
I'm sorry to drop in on you
at this late hour, Commander.
I forgot to tell you something.
Will you help me?
I've got it.
The shrines that
make up the five points
of the feng shui star
are Toshogu, Futarasan,
Okonomiya,
Manjanji, and Kazan.
These five energy points are
interacting with each other,
which means the ki
changes direction
directly below Lake Chuzenji.
Take a look.
See how the lake is
shaped like a bowl
at the base of the mountain?
It's acting like
a big basin of energy.
Are you able to figure out
just where Reisui
is hiding himself?
♪
That's got to be the spot.
Reisui has to be
in Senjogahara.
But before he went there,
he must have grabbed
the real device
and took it with him.
You're probably right,
but it's possible
somebody else has it.
The Ryu Myaku has to be
stopped before it's too late.
We have to go
to Senjogahara now.
Come on.
Jinpu!
Give your wounded foot a rest.
Take my horse.
Thanks, Sanosuke!
(chanting)
♪
They don't have the slightest
idea what's going on.
It's working out
just as I planned.
(evil laughter)
(theme song)
♪