♪
It's beautiful, isn't it?
And it will
belong to me,
all of it!
This will be
my kingdom.
It will be a
new beginning,
for all of us!
♪
Here, the Samurai
will live as men,
and the sword will
continue to rule!
(laughter)
There's great
Aunt Hannah!
Hey, this is great!
Izu is really
a nice place.
I love it here!
What a fine place
to take a vacation.
Isn't this great?
Huh?
Wait!
I'll go over
in a minute.
Ughhh!
Kori!
Dr. Gensai's
sister will
be here to meet
us any minute!
You can't faint now,
Kori, you have to get up!
Hello,
and welcome!
Greetings,
welcome to Izu!
Glad you came.
I heard wonderful
things about you
from my brother.
It's amazing how much
she looks like Dr. Gensai.
-Uh-huh.
-Yeah.
Kori, let's cross.
Take my hand.
Excuse me!
Whoa!
Ahh!
Oh!
Thanks a lot
for inviting us.
It's been a long time
since we've been
away from home.
Well, Izu is
a nice place,
a wonderful place
for a vacation.
You're welcome
to stay here as
long as you like!
Yay!
Well, in that case,
we're staying...
for a month.
I'm just kidding.
Two months.
Huh?
Will you be able
to leave the clinic
for that long?
Dr. Gensai will just have
to take care of everything.
(laughs)
That's my brother!
I can't wait
for the Master
to meet all of you.
The Master?
Yes, the Master's
very young.
If you look over there,
you can see his house.
Ah!
Young Master Yutaro
lost both his parents
when he was
very small.
He became the master
of the mansion when
he was five.
His father was
very, very wealthy.
Five years old?
That's right!
As a matter of fact,
all the land you see here
belongs to him, too.
Whoa!
It's really quite
a spread, isn't it?
♪
Man, this is sweet.
Don't get
too attached,
you'll never have
things like this.
Yeah, neither will you.
Oh, be quiet.
All of this
stuff belongs
to the young Master?
Please, forgive
me, Master,
I have tried everywhere,
but I can't find anybody.
Now I've told you,
I want to start
learning kendo as
soon as possible.
So when are you
going to find me
a teacher?
Is that the young
Master Yutaro?
Mm-hmm.
Now go on,
find me a master
swordsman who is
as good as my father.
But your late father,
Yuzaemon, was one of
the greatest master
swordsmen of all time!
I have no idea
where we could
find anyone
that good!
I don't even
know where to look.
I want to be
a great swordsman
so my father will
be proud of me.
Find someone
who measures up!
Find him right away,
or you can look
for another job.
This young master's
nothing but a brat.
You understand?
Hmm?
Good morning,
Master Yutaro.
Would you like to
meet my visitors, or...
Who are they?
Are they your relatives?
Tell them they're
welcome to stay here
as long as they like.
Uh, they are
not my relatives,
but according
to my brother,
they are some of
the best swordsmen
in the land.
Ooh, that's quite
a grip, Hannah.
This one has an
impressive title
I can't remember.
Well, he doesn't
look very tough to me.
If he's so great,
bring him over here.
Let's see
what he can do.
(Yahiko growls)
All right, then,
let's see if you can
knock this
chandelier down
with your sword.
(gasp)
My father did it
with his sword.
It's a technique
called Raijin.
As a swordsman, my father
had no equal, none.
So if you're not
as good as he is,
you're not qualified
to be my teacher.
Well, do it!
I would humbly decline.
Unfortunately,
I have no desire
to become your teacher.
What?
But I'll give you
your own house,
with servants,
if you like.
Arrgh!
Do you want a horse?
I'll get you a horse.
Ughh!!
That's it!
I can't take
this kid any longer!
You need to learn
some manners, pal!
Yahiko!
You haven't stopped
insulting people
since we've arrived here!
You can't insult
Kenshin like that!
Hey, let go of me!
You spoiled brat,
you don't deserve
Kenshin as a teacher.
Not only that,
you don't deserve
to learn how
to do kendo!
You can't speak
to him like that!
You think your money
will buy you everything!
Ha!
Ahhhhhh!
Ugh...
I'm sorry, but, uh,
there is some truth
to what Yahiko was
saying to you.
You do seem to
be pretty immature
about certain things.
Hey!
If you treat
your teacher
like a servant,
then you won't
learn anything.
A teacher must be
treated with respect.
Kendo is a
spiritual process.
Unless you change
your attitude,
you'll never have
the proper discipline
to learn the
martial arts.
How can you talk
to me like this?
You are guests
in my house!
I'm the Master!
Excuse me,
Young Master Yutaro?
But it's time to
take your daily ride.
Get out!
We'd be happy to,
Master Yutaro.
Master pain-in-the-butt!
Oh?
Don't you think
he reminds you
of someone you know?
Someone competitive
and stubborn,
just like you are?
No, not at all!
You left out the part
about them being childish.
He's probably not
such a bad guy, really.
He was brought up with
everyone treating him
like a king.
I mean, that
sort of treatment
would spoil anybody.
But I think
that underneath
all of that
is a good boy.
And with a
good teacher,
he would change
his entire attitude!
Young Master,
not so fast,
it isn't safe!
Shut up!
Who do these people
think they are,
talking to
me like that?
Ahhh!
(laughs)
Whoa, Master Yutaro,
are you all right?
His horse, get him!
Get the horse!
He's getting away!
You idiots!
Huh!
Don't kill him yet.
We have to ask
for a big ransom
from the mansion first.
And when we get it,
we won't need him anymore.
(chuckles)
Hmm?
What's wrong?
Help, help!
Yutaro's been
kidnapped!
Huh?
Don't you
know who I am?
You can't treat
me like this!
Shut up,
you little twit!
Huh?
What the...
(gasp)
Hee-ya!
♪
My father, Yuzaemon,
was a master swordsman.
His sword technique
was like lightning,
just like this.
Lighting!
Lightning...
Please, don't kill me.
Don't kill me!
Ahhh!
Ohhh...
Who did that?
Me, Kenshin Himura.
I don't believe in
senseless murder.
Yeah...
Tell me your name.
Who are you?
Raijuta...Isurugi.
Raijuta Isurugi.
You're the best
swordsman I've seen
since my father.
I want you to
be my teacher.
(clears throat)
We are honored to
have Raijuta Isurugi
as a guest
in this house.
He is a great swordsman,
and he just
saved my life.
He should be treated
with the respect that
he deserves.
You will treat him
with the respect
you would
give my father.
I won't
tolerate rudeness,
so stand up straight.
Huh?
Where are you going, Sensei?
♪
Raijuta, Sensei!
Hey!
Sensei...
I can't wait to start.
I'm really excited
about starting my
first lesson, Sensei.
Can we begin
it right now?
Can we?
Silence.
Huh?
If you want
to be great,
don't get excited.
I...all right.
Yutaro?
Uh, yes?
Kendo is serious.
It's either kill
or be killed,
it's not a game.
A bamboo sword is
a little boy's toy.
Don't ever
touch that again.
Whoa!
Oh, it's heavy.
From this day on,
you are no longer
a little boy, Yutaro.
From now on,
you will be my son.
Huh!
Ah!
We are the best
shinko style warriors.
Shinko style?
We're fellow
swordsmen of Raijuta.
You are also
a member of
the great shinko style,
a fellow swordsman,
of the honorable Raijuta.
Huh!
All hail Raijuta!
What is that?
It's aloe vera.
It's used for
medicinal purposes.
Medicine, huh?
Let's get busy fishing!
Got ya, now!
(snoring)
I didn't sleep
very well last night.
♪
This is so great,
I can't wait to get
to the hot springs and relax.
The hot water
is very good for
our aching muscles.
Right, Kenshin?
I don't recall you
doing any work that
would make your
muscles sore.
Oh, well, cutting aloe
vera plants all day
can be very tiring.
(laughs)
This is great,
I love hot springs!
Oh, it's lovely.
Oh, by the way,
I don't want to see
you guys
spying on us.
Don't worry,
we won't!
Besides, if we were
gonna peek at girls,
we'd want them
to be attractive.
I'm looking so
forward to this.
Me, too.
This is going
to feel so good.
Oh, it really is.
I know we told them
we wouldn't look...
The more they
tell us not to,
the more we want to.
Mmm.
You didn't really
think for a minute that
we would get undressed
knowing that you naughty
guys were hanging
around here, did you?
What's the
big idea?
That's no fair!
You're peeping Toms!
Oh, no, children.
Huh?
You'll have to dry
your clothes off.
it'll be dark
and chilly soon,
and you'll both catch
your death of cold!
It's snack time!
Yummy!
Mmm!
♪
That sword...
Something very strange
about all of this.
That Raijuta
Isurugi guy...
who is he,
what's his story?
So what's going
on at the mansion?
Huh?
Yutaro does
whatever Raijuta says.
And not only that,
he's brought some
other guys to stay
at the mansion.
And these men
are very rough.
Hannah, do you have
any idea who these
guys might be?
I have no idea,
but they act like
they own the place!
They've even sold off
several family treasures.
What?
They take the money
they get and buy
all kinds of
swords and spears.
They said something
about shinko style,
or something
like that.
Shinko style?
Kori, we got to go!
Huh?
We've got to help.
Yutaro is being
taken advantage of
by these swordsmen.
We've got to get him
away from Raijuta
as soon as possible!
What's the
matter with you,
what are you
standing around
looking at?
Huh? Uh...oh.
Kenshin!
Sorry, I forgot.
Kenshin's got a lot
on his mind lately.
Yeah, I guess so.
This ridge will
be our defense.
Then our kingdom
will be complete.
Raijuta, do you
really think this
man will help us?
More importantly,
do you really think
this guy--
There's no
doubt in my mind.
That guy is Battousai,
the Slasher.
♪
Yutaro?
I told you to
stay away from here.
I'm sorry.
(waves crashing)
Oh!
Are you all right?
Huh?
I think that
sword's a little bit
much for you.
Don't talk
to me like that.
I meant no disrespect.
Raijuta, did he
give you this?
Hey, don't you
touch that--
give that sword
back to me right now!
I will be just
like Raijuta,
my Sensei.
Hmm?
I'm glad
you're here,
we've been
looking for you.
Battousai!
Sensei!
You need to go
back to the mansion.
But I want to stay
with my Sensei.
Go on, Yutaro.
Go, run along.
Listen, I need
to talk to you.
Yeah?
What about?
What do you think
of this Meiji era?
Swordsmanship reduced
to nothing more than
playing with
bamboo toys.
Tradition has gone
out the window.
It's a very sad era
for us proud Samurai.
A shame.
Together, we can
change all of that,
my friend.
We want you to join us
and bring back
the sword again.
Huh?
Your legendary
slashing power
would be a great
benefit to our cause.
You should join us,
we all used to be
honorable Samurai.
We have killed
thousands of enemies.
Then came the decree
prohibiting the wearing
of swords.
That's like telling
all of us to go die!
But how can we just
lay down our swords
and become
ordinary citizens?
We cannot!
We are going to
build our own country.
What?
Under my leadership,
armies who have practiced
diligently their
sword technique
will join along
with us and destroy
the present
government.
We will take over
this land of Izu
and become an
independent nation.
You're mad.
I don't think so.
The government will
hit us with everything
they've got,
but the ridge of Izu
will act as a
natural fortress.
We are the
masters of shinko.
We can match the
power of their guns.
We'll show them all
that the martial arts
are still the most
powerful art of fighting!
Hold on!
Innocent people will
be hurt or killed
by what you do,
thousands will suffer!
The price of war!
History has
taught us one thing--
that the strong
will always reign
over the weak
and helpless.
It has always
been that way.
You are the great
Battousai only when
you are wielding
your sword.
With your powerful
sword by our side,
we could make our
kingdom a reality.
I'll pass.
What?
My reverse-edged sword
is used to protect the
weak and the suffering.
It is not for building
a selfish kingdom for you.
You are all
well-trained Samurai,
surely you can use
your abilities for good
instead of this rebellion.
You coward!
Our lives will
be destroyed
if we don't
fight against them.
Your existence as
a former slasher
will be destroyed
as well, Battousai!
I'm well aware of that.
I have already
made a decision...
To continue my
retirement from slashing--
I'll never kill again.
Too bad.
We can't let
you live now.
♪
Kill him!
(explosion)
These men are the best
of the shinko style.
They come from
all over the land.
Even the famous
Battousai the Slasher
can't take
them all on!
♪
Ahhhh!
He's amazing.
♪
Yutaro!
Ahhh!
Help!
Yutaro!
Save him, you pig!
Unfortunately,
everybody has
to die sometime
or another.
Bye bye, Battousai.
(groans)
♪