♪
(horse galloping)
Captain Sagara, I am Shindo
and I have new orders for you.
Meiji headquarters has concluded
the Sekiho troop is obsolete.
As of now, I am assuming
command of you and your company.
What?
Besides, you're
trespassing on my property.
Prepare to disband.
An ambush!
Fire!
(gunshots)
♪
(chuckles)
Gentlemen, this print of Sagara
whom we killed 10 years ago
assures us of a survivor
of the massacre.
The Sekiho troop
will take the blame
for our criminal enterprises.
♪
I didn't know
you were an art collector.
Well, actually,
I've only started
buying block prints.
And you would like me
to pick one up for you?
If you wouldn't mind,
it's already paid for.
No problem at all.
My gosh, Waiti, I think
you've got a lot of nerve.
Yeah, don't you think
Sano's got better things
to do than run errands for you?
What are you talking about?
I meant it when
I said "no problem."
That's no work
for a swordsman.
Why not? She always makes certain
that I get plenty to eat, right?
Well, actually, every
meal that I give you here
gets added to your account.
Well, I didn't know that.
Sorry, I don't have any income.
Well, I imagine
you will sometime.
Meanwhile, I'll just let
the compound interest on
all of your lunches accumulate.
Interest on lunches?
I didn't even know
I had an account!
(giggles)
Good thinking!
You got a good head for figures!
I suppose I should have known.
So, tell me about this print
you want me to pick up.
It's called "The Swordsman,"
a print by Tsukioka.
What?
I used to have
a very good friend
in the military
by the name of Sukiyoka.
This is a peculiar
way to be reminded.
(giggles)
(gasps)
Sano, are you upset?
Huh?
Uh, I hope you're not offended.
No, I'm not the least bit upset,
my little princess.
It isn't your problem.
But what isn't my problem?
Sometimes, a name is enough
to trigger profound memories.
I'll get you your print.
I'll be back.
♪
That Sanosuke sure is
a man full of surprises.
I hope he understands
I'll feed him, even if
he never has any income.
Lucky guy, huh?
♪
Do you work here?
Doesn't it look
like I work here?
Hey, Sano!
What brings you two here?
Just following the action.
And we were curious what
kind of art a swordsman likes.
How about pictures
of really cute girls?
No.
How about pictures
of cute naked girls?
Hey, you're getting
a little personal!
So, what's the big idea, mister!
Miss, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Remind me to stay
on her good side.
Whatcha want?
Oh, yeah, I have
to pick up a print for Waiti
at Lenny's restaurant.
Are you holding a print
of "The Swordsman"
by Tsukioka for
a friend of mine?
Again?
I can't keep
those prints in my shop.
I bought a whole fistful
of them from the artist.
I'm already down
to my last two.
So, who is this guy, anyway?
A very striking fellow, yeah.
I would like to have
both of these prints.
Lend me some money
for a few days, will you?
Hey, what do I
look like, a bank?
I'll pay you back.
This is a very
special situation.
Very.
How come?
When did the artist
bring you these prints?
Huh?
Well, I think it was a week ago,
this fella came by
offering me an exclusive
on that number.
I don't know why,
but some people
have shown a lot
of interest in that
piece of junk.
♪
You call this print
a "piece of junk"?
You will tell me where
the artist lives, right now!
He got a little carried away.
But now I'd say he's
coming to his senses.
I apologize if I
offended you, pal.
The artist said
he lives at 15 Murakami Place
in the slums, but he
don't like visitors.
He'll like this visitor.
I will promise you that.
What the...?
What set him off like that?
How should I know?
Mama, is it ready yet?
Very soon, sweetie, patience.
It's almost ready.
Hey!
Private Tsukioka,
member of Sagara's Elite Guard,
I know you're in there!
Thanks for your card.
It's really you!
How'd you find me?
I would have been hard to miss.
Didn't you think
I'd recognize
the portraits of me
and you with the captain?
You knew I'd see your handsome
block print eventually.
There was a chance,
I had to try.
I'm glad you're here.
Maybe this means
our work isn't over yet.
Come in, let's talk awhile.
Imagine that, they're both
surviving members of Sagara's
Democratic Elite Guard.
We should leave
them alone, Kori.
Can't we just stay and watch?
Those two soldiers oughta
have their privacy, Kori.
They deserve it.
They need room
to resolve the past
so they can face what's to come.
Karma has brought them
together for a purpose.
Come on.
Feels like a long time ago.
It was, Katsu.
Learning was a game
we played every day.
Captain Sagara made it seem
like a game so we wouldn't
resist his profound impact.
The lessons about
the value of life.
Remember that day with the fish?
Yes, I remember.
Everything seemed so easy then.
How naive we were.
He was patient with us.
Captain!
Hey, Captain!
Captain Sagara, take a look
at this great muskie we caught!
There's lots more like this one!
Hey, come on, stop wiggling!
Stop moving around so much!
Come on, stop it!
We had two other nice fish,
but they got away.
Aw, you didn't have
to tell him that, did you?
It's the truth, Sano,
that's what matters.
That's the discipline.
He taught us
to value individuals
regardless of station.
That's what he
believed in and fought for.
Yes, he gave us the dream
and then made it real for us.
(gunshots)
Even as he led our
Sekiho troop into battle
against the government tyrants,
he tried to watch out for us.
How could I forget?
Ambush!
Get down!
You two break ranks
and stay out of sight!
Begging your pardon, sir,
but we refuse to abandon
our positions,
no matter what!
We're prepared to fight
with you all the way,
Captain Sagara!
You two have learned
your lessons well.
Yeah!
♪
Huh?
No!
♪
Katsu!
I'm all right,
it didn't hurt me.
What'd you go
and do that for?
Well, why can't you pay
attention to what's going on?
Now, I guess I owe you one.
Since you're still alive,
I gather you've learned
to be more alert.
Yes, I think I'm more alert,
but I've also learned
how to stay out of trouble.
Maybe you've grown weak
in your beliefs, Sanosuke.
No, it's just that I've begun
to recognize an exercise
in futility for what it is.
"Exercise in futility,"
you call it?
Isn't that the excuse
people use for quitting
the job before it is completed?
That's the kind of talk
I'd expect from a politician.
I can't afford to believe
in the futility
of the principals
we fought for.
If I did, Captain Sagara
would have died for naught.
The Sekiho troop lives, Sano.
I hold onto that belief myself.
Listen to me well:
A belief that isn't
accompanied by action
is nothing more
than a good idea.
Action is the only
thing that counts.
It rules the day.
Maybe that's true.
Wasn't it the actions
of others that brought
about that downfall
of the Sekiho troop, Sano?
Yes.
Make a new
alliance with me, Sano.
Let's work together
to put Captain Sagara's
principles into
the kind of action
that people will really
take hold and notice.
What sort of action
did you have in mind?
Can you say?
With these bombs,
we can bring down
the corrupt government
that keeps people in bondage.
What the...?
But you can't!
Throw the tyrants out!
Have you completely
lost your mind?
It's time they paid.
First, the internal
security offices,
then the tax office,
and then the cabinet offices!
Bring them all down!
♪
When people see
that the governors
of the land are not gods,
but merely men,
the people will demand
fair and just treatment.
Katsu.
Listen, I've been preparing
for ten years to repay them
for the crimes they
committed against our captain.
Someone's got
to make them answer.
So, you're gonna blow up
the very people you want
to protect?
That makes you just
as bad as the Meiji tyrants!
Violence is the only language
that tyrants
and dictators understand.
They must be expelled,
whatever the cost,
even if that cost includes
a few innocent lives.
Katsu, you cannot
put an end to tyranny
by becoming a
vicious tyrant yourself.
The only thing
that violence begets
is even more violence.
Don't you know that yet?
I knew you once, Sano.
Your courage and passion
were equal to my own.
But now, you're
complacent and idle,
content to let jackals
rule the roost.
Katsu...
please think about
what you're saying.
I have.
So angry, sad.
Katsu is really
bent on avenging.
(explosion)
♪
What's going on here, mister?
Anybody hurt?
We are members
of the Sekiho troop.
We're stealing these goods
and we don't ever leave
any witnesses like you alive.
Oh, my God!
He means to kill us.
Run!
♪
(chuckles)
Courtesy of the Sekiho troop.
(cackles)
You're getting pretty good
at this ball bouncing bit.
Think of that,
there have been seven attacks
in five days.
"Authorities suspect
that these crimes are
being perpetrated by..."
What?
"...survivors of
the Sekiho company"?
Really?
Well, it says here
they always leave behind
a color print of Captain Sagara.
Wow, so Sano could
be involved after all!
Well, that's what I think
of your sense of humor.
Even though he borrows money
and doesn't repay it
and he mooches every meal
and he doesn't have a job
and he doesn't even look
for work, yet--
In spite of that,
he is a good guy.
Wow, to hear you guys talk,
you make Sano sound
like a real derelict.
But whatever else is true,
you know you can always
count on the guy.
Well, I know that!
Why do you suppose
that this article
in the newspaper
has got me so upset?
He's always
bragging about Sagara.
Maybe his bitterness
over the massacre
just finally caused him to snap?
Well, I still can't believe
he'd have anything to do
with robbery or murder.
You don't really supposed
he could be involved, do you?
It doesn't sound anything
like that Sano that I know.
I think that print
of Captain Sagara is the key.
Katsu?
Empty...and the bombs are gone.
♪
"Each of us must fulfill
his destiny in his own way,
my friend.
Our paths will
someday cross again.
It is meant to be."
No, he can't do it alone.
I don't know, I swear!
Have you seen the artist,
Tsunan Tsukioka?
You know that name, don't you?
New one on me.
Sorry, friend.
Thanks.
Hey, Sano, Sano!
Wait up!
What's up, guys?
You have something to tell me?
Hey, Sano, we just heard
a rumor and we thought
it might have something
to do with this guy.
You know, the one
you've been looking for?
Why, what did you hear?
There's some guy
over at the gaming parlor
who's been throwing
a lot of new money around
and claims he's
been getting rich
because of the Sekiho troop.
Sekiho?
What's this liar call himself?
Well, uh--
Shinzou!
I heard him call
himself Shinzou!
Thanks a lot
for telling me, fellas.
Hey, don't mention it.
We're on your side.
Just doing our
civic duty, you know?
No sweat, we're happy to help.
We'll see you later, Sanosuke!
I didn't give it any thought
till I read about it in
the paper like everybody else.
How was I supposed
to know they turned up
at the crime scenes?
As a matter of fact,
I really didn't even like
the prints when I first saw 'em.
I took them off
his hands as a favor.
And so, what you're saying
is someone came along
and bought the whole
lot of them, right?
You got a name or a description?
Who was your customer?
He bought only one
print to start with,
then he came back later
and took the rest of what I had.
When he did come back,
he had this great big
nasty-looking fellow with him.
Nobody used any names.
What was I supposed to do, huh?
They said I'd be
in real big trouble
if I told anybody about it.
You'll be
in trouble if you don't.
Oh, great, snake eyes!
All right, new shooter!
Look out now!
Ante up, gentlemen!
I'll never get used to losing,
even if I already have
more money that I can count!
Hey buddy, you're on
a real losing streak!
Can't hack it, huh?
It'd really bother me,
but it doesn't seem
to bother you at all.
You're a cool customer, pal.
Oh, yeah.
The Sekiho deal
I got is real sweet.
(humming)
A sweet deal, is it?
I'd like a piece of that action.
Who wants to know?
Let's skip
the formal introductions.
Tell me all about
the Sekiho troop scam
and who's behind it.
Like hell I will!
They set you up
to be the patsy, Shinzou!
Nobody sets up Shinzou!
Don't waste my precious time!
Lives are at stake,
just tell me what I
want to know!
♪
He's late.
Where is this man?
I'll send someone to look.
Oshira, go find Shinzou now!
Drag him in here!
Yes, sir!
Never mind, let him wander back.
Yes, sir.
Have you thoroughly
scouted out next target?
Indeed we have.
The art collection of Shimizu
will bring us a nice fat income.
The local police
have been advised
to stay away
until after midnight.
Mm-hmm, excellent.
Meanwhile, I have
used my position
in the Meiji government
to spread disinformation,
it keeps them away from us.
So it would seem,
but we still need more time.
The images of Captain Sagara
will keep prying eyes away
from us long enough.
But don't you think
someone's bound to see through
our subterfuge eventually?
When we're done.
It is fortunate that
a massacre survivor
should provide us
with a cover for our activities.
Not to mention, he's given
us the perfect calling card.
Wait.
It would be unwise
to take too much for granted.
Men of deep conviction should
always be considered dangerous.
Twenty years as
a provincial policeman
taught me all I need to know
about the dangers of morality.
Shinzou!
Long time no see.
Who the hell are you?
A rumor says that
you're the man who ordered
your mercenaries to fire
on Captain Sagara's company
by authority of
the Meiji government
and that you've used
your position of authority
to advance your
criminal activities!
I said who are you?
Surviving Sekiho trooper,
Sanosuke Sagara.
What?
Sagara?
What do you want, trooper?
My demands are simple,
few in number,
and not negotiable.
I plan to see to it
that your crime spree is over,
to see that complete restitution
is made to all of the victims
and their families,
and to see you in jail!
Nobody talks to me
like that and lives
to brag about it, sonny!
I'll see your head roll!
Attack!
♪
Well, don't just
stand there, you idiots!
Get him!
♪
Oh, yeah?
Watch a master at work.
♪
All right, I think this'll help!
Now, cut him down!
♪
Small world.
Hey, I bumped into
the most interesting
art dealer downtown
who was telling me
all about some "Sekiho troop."
I heard that, too.
I think it's time
we showed these clowns
what some real
Sekiho troopers can do.
Hey, what do you say, Katsu?
Just what I had in mind.
♪
Come on, let's do it!
Take that!
Place your bets!
♪
Have a nice day.
I love it when a plan works.
Same here.
There's just one more rat
that we have to put in the cage.
Just hold on there, troopers!
You boys think you've
accomplished something?
Well, you haven't.
I'll tell you exactly
what we've got here.
Just another raid
on a private residence
by the Sekiho troop.
Your dead bodies here on my lawn
will be proof enough.
Thanks for dropping by.
Katsu!
♪
Well, looks like
you haven't learned
a thing in ten years, have you?
I guess I haven't,
and I thought you said
you were much more alert.
All right, Sergeant,
break it down.
You inside, surrender!
The house is surrounded!
♪
Thank you, Sanosuke,
for your faith in me.
Sure thing.
♪
You too.
I guess I was talking
pretty crazy there
for a while, huh?
A bit.
I was in a really dark
place for a long time.
Yeah.
I never realized how
deep my shock was.
The Captain was
such a hero for me
that the only thing I could
think about for all those years
was someday,
some glorious day,
when I paid back the monsters
who had cut him down
in the warm, sweet summer
of his life.
Well...I'll be seeing you.
So, you gonna be okay?
♪
Yeah, you're okay.
Sano!
Try to stay out
of trouble, will ya?
"Our work is not
yet done, my friend."
♪