♪
(singing in foreign language)
(water flowing)
♪
(gasping)
(birds chirping)
♪
Oh my.
Just take a look at that.
Hey guys, come over here!
♪
That thing is huge!
Whoa, you're not kidding.
♪
(indistinct remarks)
We have to take a boat
from here to Shimabara?
That's right.
I have to go to Shimabara,
and do what I can
to stop Shogo Amakusa.
I swore an oath to
Master Hiko that I would.
So, Kenshin, are you
going to Shimabara?
Mhm.
Before Hyoei died,
he told me all about Shogo.
He said that Shogo was insane,
and that he will create
a bloodbath in Shimabara.
-I cannot allow that.
-Good.
Somebody needs to stand up
to this deranged zealot
Shogo Amakusa
before it's too late.
Himura, you appear to be the
best candidate for the job.
I'm glad you're
going and not me.
Huh?
As the 13th successor of
the Hiten Mitsurugi style,
I cannot allow Shogo to succeed,
but since I taught you
the secret principle
which you used to defeat
Shishio, I feel that you
should prevent Shogo's warped
plan from taking effect.
I am grateful to you,
and I said I would do it.
♪
Huh, Shimabara.
This fight will not
be easy, Himura.
-You know that.
-I know.
Shogo's a master
swordsman, be careful.
♪
(bell tolling)
These guys are small.
Hey, these European people
are really tiny, aren't they?
Those are dolls,
you naive knucklehead.
Wow, are those dresses on sale?
-She's gonna drive me nuts!
-Look at the pretty pictures!
Oh, there are music
boxes over there!
Misao's giving me a headache.
Kenshin, why'd you have
to bring that wacky girl
along on this trip anyway?
Okina wanted her
to come along with us.
Besides, she can utilize the
Oni gang's information network.
Yeah, but is she gonna help
us or just get in the way?
Guys, I found a bakery
with lots of cake!
Did I just hear her say cake?
Yahoo!
I love cake,
I could eat it all!
-Ah!
-Yoshi!
Whoa!
We're sorry about that,
Governor, are you all right?
Yes, yes, I'm fine.
You idiot, you could've
been squashed like a bug.
Ow.
I'm terribly sorry, are
you all right, young man?
Oh, well--Dr. Elston?
Why, Kenshin Himura!
♪
It's nice to meet you,
Governor Elston.
I had no idea Kenshin had
such powerful friends.
You see, young lady, Kenshin
Himura is my lifesaver.
When I stayed in Choshu at
the end of the Tokugawa era,
there was an
anti-foreigner movement
among some of the people there.
One night, I was
attacked by several thugs.
Only one man came to
my rescue that night.
Our Kenshin Himura.
Now he's the Governor General
of the Dutch Consulate,
but at the time of the attack,
Dr. Elston was a dedicated
doctor who traveled
the countryside to cure
many poor sick people.
Kenshin has told me about all
of those people that you helped.
-Ow!
-Hello, sir.
So, this must be the
great Kenshin Himura
that I've heard so much about.
Yes, this is Kenshin.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Mr. Santo.
He's my assistant.
♪
Pleasure to meet you.
I understand that you're
going to Shimabara.
Word travels fast around here.
Dr. Elston, I need
to ask you something.
Have you heard of
anything strange
happening in Shimabara lately?
Such as?
For instance, any talk
of an upcoming battle?
Now where would you
get such a strange idea
as that, Mr. Himura?
Shimabara is known
as a peaceful area.
He's right, they're
a peaceful people,
but Shimabara has a sad history
of suppressing Christianity.
I'm afraid it was quite
a tragic situation.
All the conventions of
Christianity, and any form
of practicing that religion
was strictly forbidden.
Now, Himura, if you find
out that anything unsavory
is going on in Shimabara,
please let me know about it.
I want to protect the people.
I am a politician who believes
fervently in free democracy,
and the precious
rights of the people.
I also believe in
freedom of religion,
and as a matter of fact, I
myself am I devoted Christian.
♪
(crickets chirping)
Boy, I just couldn't wait
to get out of there.
I can't stand being
around the upper crust.
Whoa.
Uh, sorry.
(crickets chirping)
They know better
than to mess with me.
(grunting)
Why didn't I give
it back to her?
♪
You had to butt in to something
that was none of your business.
Goodbye.
You think you're
better than everyone.
You think you're above
it all, don't you, lady?
♪
Shogo, my brother.
Do you--do you think I'm
better than everybody else?
Do I act like I'm above it all?
Somebody had the nerve
to say that to me.
I'm not like that, am I?
♪
-Sayo.
-What, Shogo?
What did you do
with your medallion?
(sighing)
My medallion.
A friend of mine's
holding it for me.
I'll get it back
from him very soon.
You're not a very
good liar, sister.
♪
You really haven't
changed very much, Sayo.
You're still just a little girl.
♪
Why, thank you, Shozo.
You are welcome,
my most holy mother.
This is for you.
Oh my, what a beautiful flower.
Do you like it?
Yes, it's quite a
lovely flower, Shozo.
It's so pure.
(crickets chirping)
Just like you.
Lovely and pure.
Welcome home,
savior of the people.
Kaio has ordered
us to have a boat
ready and waiting for you
for you travel to Shimabara.
♪
Shogo is close at hand.
He will be arriving here
very shortly, Kaio.
♪
We celebrate the life
and living with blood.
With blood we celebrate.
(laughing)
(bell chiming)
Shogo has returned.
Shogo has returned!
Shogo has turned the
day into darkness!
Shogo has returned.
♪
(indistinct conversations)
-Out there!
-There he is!
♪
Listen, my people.
The miracle Shogo
calls to happen
was prophesized
in this holy book.
This holy book was written
by an anonymous
Portuguese minister.
He preached that
in our Meiji era,
a child of God will appear.
He will create miracles
with the power he receives
from God.
(indistinct remarks)
♪
Behold, a miracle!
(crowd gasping)
♪
Look, it's a miracle!
He must be the child of God.
(indistinct murmuring)
♪
Did you see that?
Shogo is the master
of all miracles.
He is truly our savior.
Shogo will expel all evil, and
change this degenerate world
of ours into his
own God's country.
He's right, Shogo
truly is our savior!
He will save us from evil!
Yeah, he will build
us God's country!
Yes, Shogo!
(all chanting)
Shogo will save us!
♪
Pardon me, Your Grace,
but your revenge in Japan
was executed
beautifully as usual.
That fire, miracle stuff.
I suppose that was
your lame idea, Kaio.
Didn't you like it, Your Grace?
No, I did not.
But Shogo, the village people
were very impressed by it.
They truly enjoy
seeing their savior
create a blazing
fire on the water.
Another miracle to go along with
turning daylight into night.
These villagers are
ready to sacrifice
their lives for their savior.
Enough, Kaio.
Let me make one thing
perfectly clear, Kaio.
I don't need cheap tricks
to make God's country.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Hm?
Sir, we've heard from Mr. Santo.
He tells us
Battousai the Slasher
is planning to
come to Shimabara.
He thinks because
he defeated Shishio
that he can defeat
the great Shogo.
He is sadly mistaken.
He is a nuisance that
has to be dealt with.
I want you to take
care of him, Hachizo.
What should I do?
♪
-Just kill him.
-Yes, sir.
You can try to kill him,
but no one will able to
defeat Himura except me.
♪
(water flowing)
Well, here we are in Shimabara.
Yes, we finally
made it, Sanosuke.
I brought along some
documents and maps
that Master Hyoei left
me before his death.
According to these,
Shogo has established
some sort of secret kingdom here
with himself as the emperor.
Really?
Yeah, as a matter of fact,
I think we can probably
even find the place tonight.
All right then, Kenshin,
I'll go by myself.
I'll see you later.
Where do you think you're going?
We have Oniwabanshu double
agents working in Shimabara.
I'm going to make contact,
and get some information.
I'll meet you back here.
Kenshin, I hope you
knock his block off.
Hey, what's your hurry?
Whoa, I didn't know she
could move like that.
Incredible!
Kori, I want you and Yoshi
to wait here for us.
Does that sound good?
Sure, but what are you
going to do, Kenshin?
Sano and I are
gonna check it out.
We'll return later.
-Be careful!
-We will.
See ya.
(waves crashing)
I don't get it.
All of these people come here
because they really think
that Shogo is the child of God,
and they're gonna help him build
his dream country or
whatever it's called?
-People need hope.
-Huh?
While the law
banning Christianity
is no longer in effect,
the sadness of the people
of Shimabara is not over yet.
Many people have
been brutally murdered
just because they
believed in Jesus Christ.
The ones who survived had
to worship God secretly.
For many of them, the answer
to their hopes and dreams
was to have their savior appear.
And to many believers, that's
exactly what Shogo represents.
Hey, Kori, are you trying
to tell me that you believe
that Shogo is some kind
of great savior too?
Certainly not, Yoshi.
It's just--I can
imagine how they feel.
They must be reaching
out for anything.
Huh?
Should we go back
to the village,
and let them know
that they're here?
What do you think?
I don't know.
-Let's just see who they are.
-Get down!
-Huh?
Don't do that again.
If they catch us they
might even kill us.
(crying)
-They're a bunch of kids.
-Yeah!
Do you think those kids know
anything about Shogo Amakusa?
I don't know.
(whining)
Hey, Kori!
All of you should
leave our homeland!
Why you!
Oh, I wanna go home!
Huh?
(grunting)
Why, you!
Yoshi!
They dropped their medallion.
Hey, wait up!
Huh, I wonder where those
darn little buggers went?
Kori?
Kori's disappeared, but
where could she have gone?
Hello?
Is there anyone here?
(rustling)
(gasping)
Oh my, this a secret passageway!
(water dripping)
(gasping)
(groaning)
(screaming)
This is unbelievable.
I had no idea something like
this could be down here.
According to the map that
Master Hyoei gave to me,
the main church is supposed to
be hidden deep underground--
Wait a minute, did you
just say a church?
During the Tokugawa era when
Christianity was illegal,
church members practiced their
faith in secret down here.
It was a safe place for them.
As a matter of
fact, Shira Amakusa
worshipped here 250 years ago.
I can't believe it,
that's amazing.
I don't understand
how they managed
to keep this place
a secret all this time.
All the worshippers
were sworn to secrecy.
Stop where you are,
you're right.
It is a secret, one that you
will carry to your grave.
(laughing)
♪
Check him out, can you
believe this guy, Kenshin?
I think he's been
down here too long.
He doesn't know who
he's dealing with.
Don't tell me.
You're Battousai the Slasher.
That's right, fat man,
and I'm Sanosuke Sagara!
Oh, you mean that little
guy is the famous evil?
Evil?
Would you mind telling
us just who you are?
Ha, you'll find out soon enough.
♪
(growling)
(laughing nervously)
What do we do now, Kenshin?
Die, evil!
(barking)
♪
There's too many of them!
Sano, let's go!
We'll split up, then
we'll turn around,
and try to take them
one at a time.
Okay.
♪
These damn dogs,
I can't shake 'em!
I guess they're faster
than we thought!
♪
(yelling)
Uh-oh.
(laughing)
You, the evil,
must be destroyed.
Otherwise all of us
worshippers will be killed.
I am not the evil.
You will die!
♪
(shouting)
(panting)
Huh?
♪
This is a church.
Dearest Lord,
I beseech Thee to
accept my offering,
the sacrifice of
Kenshin Himura's life,
for Your good and the good
of all Your Christian people.
♪
How strange.
(singing in foreign language)
♪