♪
(bell tolling)
(insects chirping)
(water rushing)
Sanosuke?
Hmm?
Ahh!
Oh, I see, you're
just hanging around.
What are you, crazy?
I could've fallen over, huh?
(harp playing)
Wow.
Who are you, anyway?
Why, you silly boy,
it's little old me, Misao!
So, what do you think
of my new outfit?
Isn't it fantastic?
I wanted to look just like
all of the elegant ladies
in Nagasaki!
What do you think?
Well, you look great!
For Misao.
Hey Sano, who's that lovely
dish you're talking to?
She's not a lovely dish,
she's Misao!
Why don't we all go and feast
on some gourmet cuisine?
No thanks, Misao,
I'd rather go and eat some food,
if it's all the same to you.
Hey, Sano, aren't
you going with us?
Nah, I'm staying here.
Hey, you guys, what's
wrong with Sano anyway?
I mean, even though
the whole incident is over,
he stares like this,
just looking up
to the sky like he's
waiting for some answer.
Yeah, I think you're
right about that,
he's been acting
really strange lately.
It's not like him
to turn down a free meal.
-I wonder if he--
-Hmm?
If he's still
thinking about Sayo?
Isn't that Lady Magdalia?
Mm-hmm.
Could you wait here for a while?
(footsteps)
Sanosuke?
Hi, Kori, what is it?
It's just, well...
What is it?
It's about Lady Magdalia.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
She seemed nice.
And you tried so hard,
you did everything you could
to save her life.
You can't hold yourself
responsible this time.
It was just her time
to go, Sanosuke.
Sometimes things
are just meant to be,
and no matter how hard we try,
there's nothing we can do
to change them.
All I know is she's gone now.
Where's the justice in that?
Wait, Sano!
I'm going to see
Shogo at the jail
and I was wondering if perhaps
you would like to join me.
Sano?
You're seeing Shogo?
That's right,
Dr. Elsten
gave me a visitation permit
to go to the jail and see him!
I thought that maybe
he could use a little
cheering up.
I need you to help me out.
(gasp)
I really need you to
get this letter to him.
Could you do that for me, Kori?
What is it?
It's a letter.
Lady Magdalia asked me
to make sure he got this.
It's her farewell to Shogo.
(gasp)
Please take it to him.
Hmm...
(footsteps)
Dr. Elsten?
That's really terrible.
Yes, but I'm afraid
it's true, Kenshin.
The Japanese government
is still debating
about what to do
with Shogo Amakusa
and the remaining 88 villagers.
I think that they will exile
all of the villagers,
but what I'm really afraid of
is that they will
sentence Shogo to death.
How unjust!
Hasn't he suffered enough?
His father was brutally murdered
right in front of his eyes,
his mother and his sister
died from a horrible disease,
he's made to renounce
everything he believes in,
and still they
want to punish him?
He should be allowed to live,
he should be shown compassion,
especially for all
those who love him.
Listen, Kenshin, I promise
that I will use all of my
influence to save Shogo.
Great.
In my capacity as
the acting Dutch consul,
I have forwarded my request
to free Shogo to
the Japanese government.
They should reply today.
All we can do is pray for
Shogo's release and freedom.
(door opening)
You'll have to hurry, Miss Kori,
you're not allowed
a lot of time to see him.
You'll have to leave
when I say, understand?
Yes.
(footsteps)
(cell door unlocking)
Hmm?
Uh, hello.
Hey, Kori, is that you?
It's awfully nice
of you to come.
Well...
♪
(door closes)
I just came from
the villagers.
Everybody was fine,
they all asked about you.
They told me that
they still believe in you
and that has given
them great strength.
They said they have nothing
to fear in the future.
Kenshin told me
that you had met
Master Hiko when
you were just a child.
He said that you must have
really understood and mastered
the teachings of
the Hiten Mitsurugi style,
because your first impulse
is to help and protect people.
I understood what he meant
when I saw the people
of the village.
You can be proud of what
you've accomplished
for your people, Shogo.
Thank you, Kori.
Hiten Mitsurugi style
taught me all kinds
of great things to be
an enriched person.
But I don't think I'll ever
pick up another sword again.
♪
If I am ever able
to leave this place alive,
I will dedicate my life
to helping people.
And I will do this
without the help
of a sword.
Mm-hmm.
Shogo, Sanosuke asked me
to give this to you.
It's a letter
to you from Sayo!
I really wish I could've
known her better,
but there just wasn't the time.
I really felt we had
a lot in common
even though I only
met her that once.
I know that we would
have been best friends,
I just wish I could
talk to her right now!
If only she didn't have to...
Oh, I'm sorry,
I didn't mean
to make you sad.
Time's up, you have to go!
Okay.
Sorry, I have to leave now.
If Sayo was here...
I'm certain you two
would've been good friends.
She would've
greatly admired you.
You two would have
been very close.
♪
Thanks for coming here.
(sigh)
Huh?
♪
Mr. Kawaji!
I didn't expect to see you here!
I didn't expect
to see you, either.
What are you doing here, Himura?
Actually, Mr. Kawaji,
I'm a guest
of Dr. Elsten
of the Dutch consulate.
Dr. Elsten is inside
negotiating with
the acting governor
of Nagasaki.
Right now,
they're deliberating
on the punishment
to Shogo Amakusa
and his group.
The sad part is,
is that this whole
incident started
because of innocent
people being persecuted.
If they try to repress
these people again
I fear the same mistake
will be repeated.
I really don't understand
why our people can't get along.
Tell me something,
have you brought
an official notice
from the government?
Is that the reason why
you've come here now,
Mr. Kawaji?
That's right.
You don't have to
worry, Mr. Himura.
We don't want to sacrifice
any more lives than we have to.
There's been enough
bloodshed here already.
The Japanese government
realizes that.
But this Shogo
has broken the law.
He leaves us no choice
except to punish him
for his crimes
against the nation.
The government has
made its decision
and I must deliver it to
Dr. Elsten and the governor.
Don't let me stop
you, Mr. Kawaji.
I know they are awaiting
the decision anxiously.
It was good to see
you again, Himura.
♪
(door opens)
I'm here to give you notice.
This is the formal decision
from the Japanese government
regarding Shogo.
We will not permit
Shogo Amakusa
and his 88 followers
to stay here in Japan.
They must be exiled
overseas immediately.
Understood?
But tell me,
is there any country
that will readily
accept all of them?
My country would be
glad to allow Shogo--
Now, hold on a second!
No, Captain.
This is the final decision
by the Japanese government.
There is to be no discussion!
If Dr. Elsten's nation
will accept Shogo
and his followers,
that's good enough
for us!
Mm-hmm.
♪
I keep my promise to you,
Lady Magdalia.
Your people will have a home.
♪
Oof!
Why did you interfere?
I did not want
you to help me!
Ouch, that hurts!
What are you doing, anyway?
Would you please hold still
and stop fidgeting for a minute?
Would you hurry up already?
You know, you are
a whole lot rougher
than your Christian
followers would think!
Please don't move, Sano.
I am still,
and don't think
you can judge me!
Besides, you don't know
everything about me anyway.
I know who you are.
You're easy to figure out.
Oh look, there's
another wound there!
Huh?
Oh.
♪
I give you my word
that I will take care
of Lady Magdalia.
All right, I'll trust you then.
(panting)
I can't let you die.
I promised Shozo that
I would protect you.
Please, please don't die!
Thanks for everything, Sanosuke.
Thank you for everything.
I will never forget you.
Don't give up now!
You have to try and live,
I can't let you go!
You just can't die
without me knowing
your real name!
Sayo...
...my real name is Sayo.
It's Sayo.
Sanosuke,
I'm so glad
to have met you.
Please stay with me.
Sayo, Sayo?
Sayo...
♪
(footsteps)
Shozo, you're alive!
I'm glad to see you!
Ugh!
(smack)
Ahh!
(grunting)
Hey Shozo, what did
you hit me for?
(panting)
You had said that
you would protect Sayo,
you gave us your word,
you said you
wouldn't let her die!
You gave me your promise,
and I trusted you!
And now, now she's dead,
isn't she?
I would do anything in the world
to get her back.
I know inside that you did
the very best you could.
Lady Magdalia knows
that you kept your promise.
Ugh...
But why, why did you punch me?
I wanted to blame
you for her death,
but I know it wasn't your fault.
You sure have
a funny way
of showing it.
♪
I really miss her.
She was someone very special.
You have no idea how special.
♪
Hey, Sanosuke.
Hmm?
I, uh...
...I've gone against
Lady Magdalia's teachings
only once in my life.
I killed a man.
I had to.
♪
(whoosh)
I will try to make
restitution for that
all the rest of my life.
I will do everything in
my power to help people.
I think only in that way,
Lady Magdalia will forgive me.
She would.
She was forgiving.
♪
Here, lady, look
what I brought you.
♪
Do you remember this flower?
It's pure, and beautiful,
just exactly like you were,
Lady Magdalia.
I miss you so.
You were my world.
I'll always...
...remember you
and your kindness.
Goodbye, goodbye!
(sobbing)
♪
(fluttering)
"Shogo Amakusa
has changed his name
back to Shogo Muto.
He's given up the sword.
The government of Japan
has exiled him and his people,
so they will be going
across the ocean
to live permanently in Holland.
All my best, Kenshin."
So Shogo decided to put
down his sword forever.
(sipping)
Ahh.
You've made me proud,
Kenshin Himura.
You got Shogo
to turn away
from his dark side
and walk into the light.
♪
(seagulls cawing)
Here we are,
how do you like our ship?
Hey, we're going to Holland,
we're going to Holland!
I can't wait till we set sail!
We're taking a long trip!
There'll be lots of
things to do there!
Ooh, this is a big boat!
They're going to Holland,
that'll be great!
Oh, I wish I could go, too!
Kenshin, would you
like to go with us?
Thank you, Genemon, but I
think I'll stay in Japan.
I guess you're not
as adventurous
as I thought you were.
(laughs)
Excuse me there,
so is Holland
over this way?
Or is it over that way?
Well, I don't know.
Don't worry, my friend.
I'll show you everything.
It will take us about
three months to get there.
I'll be your personal
guide, all right?
Oh, thank you,
that's very kind
of you, sir, thank you.
♪
(paper unfolding)
"My dear brother,
I don't know when
you'll have the opportunity
to read this letter,
but I wanted the chance
to say goodbye.
I feel the end is near,
and I don't have much time left.
I want to tell you how I feel,
and that is why I wanted
to write this to you.
It's so strange that my life
is coming to an end.
It seems like it
went by so fast.
I still feel like I've got
so much more left to do.
I think about all
of the good times
we had together.
I think about our time in China,
and about you
teaching me about God,
teaching me what our
father taught you.
Whenever I would cry,
you were always
so gentle with me.
I was usually sad
because I missed
our family so.
You always reminded me
that they were there
in spirit,
watching over me
like loving angels.
Dear brother,
your love and guidance
and support helped mold me
into the young woman
that I am today.
Shogo...
I couldn't have made it
without you.
♪
And now,
as the sun sets
on my life,
I want you
to promise me
that you will shed
your tears for people
who are hurt.
Give emotional support
to those who are sad
and help the weak,
because I believe
that after I have gone,
you will make our
dreams come true.
You are the light of hope,
dear brother.
Preserve the dream
of our father and mother
and Uncle Hyoei,
that all men and women
can work, have food,
take care of each other,
and treat each other
with respect and dignity
and honor.
When the going gets tough,
you can always remember me
watching you from above,
cheering you on,
wanting you to succeed.
Remember everything
that you have done.
Be proud in the knowledge that
you have already helped people.
I am so proud of you.
It's time to say goodbye,
my brother.
I couldn't have asked
for a better brother
on this earth.
I love you."
Sayo...
I'll never forget you,
my dear sister.
It's time to leave, Shogo.
Ahoy, landlubbers!
Is everyone on board
that's going with us?
-Hey, hold on!
-Huh?
(panting)
I'm glad we made it!
You've got too much luggage!
Sorry it's so heavy,
but those bags
contain my life's possessions.
My memories are in there!
Everything from my late husband,
how can I leave that?
I can never come
back ever again!
You can never come back?
That's not true, Matsu.
You'll come back some day.
Attention, everyone,
the ship is leaving now.
Thank you for everything,
my dear friends.
(gong chiming)
Have a nice trip, Shozo!
Thanks, Sano!
Goodbye!
He's a good guy.
I hope I see him again someday.
Shogo's coming aboard!
Yeah, look, there he is!
♪
Himura...
...I wanted to thank you
for everything you've done
for me and my people.
Mm-hmm.
I will really miss
our friendship, Kenshin.
So will I.
Hmm?
♪
(water rushing)
(crowd shouting goodbyes)
♪
Goodbye, my home.
I will never set foot
on your soil again.
Live in peace.
Holland?
That seems so far away!
It is, but it's
a beautiful country
and they'll have a fresh start.
It won't be easy,
but Shogo is with them
and he will guide them
and help them make
the transition into
their nice new home.
They're getting what they need
and Shogo will get to do
the one thing he wants
to do more than anything
in this whole world.
Shogo Muto will finally be able
to make Lady Magdalia's
dearest dream come true.
♪