♪
(singing in foreign language)
The injuries
that you sustained
in your battle with Shishio
seem to be healing
very well, Kenshin.
I'm just going
to change this bandage
because you don't want
to risk an infection.
Thanks, Megumi.
You're welcome.
But listen,
Kenshin, next time,
if you're silly enough
to get hurt like this again,
I am not going to be
your nursemaid, understand?
Yes, I promise to be much
more careful from now on.
♪
Huh?
I just don't want to see
anything happen to you.
Some things we can't control.
♪
(birdsong)
You're going to do what?
You're going back home?
Why so soon?
We have to.
Aoi-Ya has just been restored
and I was really hoping
we could have
some fun together!
Don't get me wrong, Misao,
we've enjoyed
your generous hospitality
and would like to stay longer.
But it's important that
I get back home right away
and open up my dojo.
Oh, come on,
what's the hurry,
you only have one student,
it's not like
anyone's gonna miss it!
No one cares about
that beat-up old place!
I'm going to forget
you ever said that, Misao,
but if you say it again,
I'll tear you apart.
You don't want
to mess with me
if you know
what's good for you.
Well, tomorrow
is awfully sudden.
Say, I've got an idea.
Why don't you stay
for the Obon Festival,
that's something
you shouldn't miss.
I forgot about that,
why don't we all go, hmm?
Well, I would,
but unfortunately
we've already purchased
our tickets for the train
-and also--
-Yeah, what is it?
You see, this place has many
bitter memories for Kenshin.
He needs to rest
and get away
from it for a while.
That's the real
reason we have to go.
(birdsong)
Kori's right, Kenshin
was once known as Battousai.
He's always going
to have to live with that.
But that was
all in the past.
Kenshin's not
like that anymore.
He's a new person
and he should
be proud of himself.
He needs to put those
memories behind him.
He's been through so
much, it'll take time.
Don't you understand?
Understand--come on, Kori,
it's time for Kenshin
to get on with his life!
He's got to quit
being so negative!
Otherwise, he's gonna
drive himself crazy!
I just don't want
to take a chance.
That's enough already,
quit making such a fuss.
You should trust your elders.
I'll tell you
what you should do.
Let's spend the day
doing up the town.
Huh?
Come on,
let it all hang out!
We'll walk on the wild side.
Forget our troubles,
let's have fun!
Maybe I'll get a geisha.
(laughing)
Excuse me,
what kind of tea
did you say
you were drinking?
Well, I suppose we do
deserve some fun after all.
I'll go wake up the others.
I'm sorry, but Kenshin
and Sano aren't here,
they've gone someplace.
Do you happen to know
where they went?
Did they go off together?
They weren't together.
Kenshin left first
and I have no idea
where they went.
You know, I think I'll do
some sightseeing myself.
What, where are you going?
Come back here.
The least you can do
is tell me
where you're going.
Mount Hiei.
The mountain?
See you.
Yoshi, hey,
wait a minute!
-Uh, Kori.
-Huh?
Where did Kenshin go?
What's the big idea,
you startled me, Megumi.
I'm really sorry about
that, I didn't mean to.
But I was hoping
to talk to you.
Could we spend
some time together?
There's something I wanted
to talk to you about.
It's always hard
to leave friends behind,
but I really couldn't
wait to get back home.
Kenshin needed time to heal
and this city only held
grim reminders of the past.
But first he had to
make peace with himself
and pay his respects
to those that have
fallen along the way.
-Excuse me.
-Oh?
Those are very
beautiful flowers.
I'd like to buy some.
I'm taking them
to an old friend.
Kori!
Okina and I are getting
ready to go into town.
Where are you?
Huh, she's not here.
Oh, damn, the old man's
gonna be very disappointed
to hear about this.
Huh, what?
Aoshi!
I could help you,
if only you'd let me.
I've just got
to see it for myself.
The exact spot where
Kenshin fought Shishio.
Wow, what a mess!
This place used to be
Shishio's hideout.
Now look at it.
I guess this is
all that's left here.
Hmm.
It really burns me up
that I couldn't
be here to see it.
(insects chirping)
Huh, grrr!
Looks like someone
got left behind.
Huh?
You?
What in the heck
are you doin' here?
When Megumi asked
to speak to me,
I wasn't sure how to react.
We had never been
the best of friends.
I didn't know if
I could really trust her.
But we had something
in common: Kenshin.
I knew she cared about him
just as much as I did.
I could see there was
something troubling her,
but I couldn't
figure out what it was.
So, Yoshi, you're trying
to tell me you came here
just to have
a look at the place?
Yeah, that's right.
I needed to see it
with my own eyes.
Well, I'm glad you did,
because otherwise
I wouldn't have been able
to devour this
scrumptious lunch.
This is absolutely
delicious, who was the chef,
it wasn't you, was it?
No way, Omasu made it.
Well, that figures.
I wish Kori knew
how to cook like this.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Sano?
Hm?
It bothers me
that I wasn't allowed
to be there to help Kenshin.
It made me feel
left out, you know?
What are you
talking about, Yoshi?
You defeated a member
of the Juppongatana
all by yourself
and protected everyone.
How is it possible
that you feel as if
you've been left out, huh?
Because, I never
had the opportunity
to get a first-hand look
into that bastard's eyes.
and I'm talking
about Shishio.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Ow, what's that for?
Because you're a kid.
Sano!
I'm taking you to the place
where Kenshin and Shishio
had their battle.
Will that satisfy you?
(water lapping)
Megumi, before
you say anything,
I'd like to thank you
for coming all this way
to be with us.
I honestly don't know
what I would have done
if you hadn't been here
to treat Kenshin.
There's no need
to thank me, Kori.
You asked me
to come and I did.
I'm just doing my job.
I appreciate it.
It makes me
feel better to know
that I can rely on you
at times like this.
It means a lot.
That's all well and good,
but what's going to
happen the next time
Kenshin gets injured?
It may be much more
than I can handle.
Who'll take care of him then?
What do you mean, Megumi?
Just because Kenshin
is a superb athlete
doesn't mean that
he's a super human being
that's immune
from getting hurt.
It's just not true.
He's just an
ordinary human being
like the rest of us, Kori.
He can't go on
getting beat up
without it taking a
dangerous toll on his body.
If he keeps abusing himself,
the effects will
begin to accumulate.
This is serious.
He may have made
it through this fight,
but what about the next?
And Kori,
I wouldn't be surprised
if he managed to get himself
killed the next time.
What I'm telling you is true.
He was just lucky,
that's all.
He can't keep
pushing the limits.
This place hasn't
changed in ten years.
It's the same as
it's always been.
Dear friend, you've
gone on to a better life.
(insects chirping)
(wind blowing)
(rain falling)
Oh no, it's raining.
I sure hope that
Yoshi will get back
without getting all drenched.
Huh?
Misao, come back here.
Aoshi, he'll get wet.
I've got to hurry.
Aoshi kept mainly to himself,
often sneaking away
to meditate alone.
It was his way of coping
with the pain of losing,
and it offered some
semblance of comfort to him.
Yes, there must be a reason.
A reason that
I was placed here.
But I don't know why.
You know I have to admit
I was really happy
after I beat that
bat guy to a pulp.
You know I really thought
I was some kind
of a superman.
But I didn't know
how foolish I was
until Kenshin told me
that being strong
and being right
were two different things.
He made me come
to the realization
there's still a lot
of things out there
I need to learn about.
I learned sometimes we're
not as smart as we think.
Hey, I'm not gonna argue
with you about that one.
You won't be surprised
if he gets killed
the next time?
That's what I said, Kori.
Megumi, that's not
gonna happen to Kenshin.
It could.
Kenshin survived this time,
but his next fight
could have
an extremely
different outcome.
Huh?
A doctor will only
be able to do so much.
Eventually,
Kenshin's condition
will begin to deteriorate.
The strain of battle
will get to him
and he will become
weak and vulnerable.
And once he dies,
he'll be gone forever.
Impossible.
I knew Megumi was right.
No one can come
back from the dead,
yet Kenshin held a small,
impossible hope
that it could be true.
All those that he
had killed needlessly
were coming back
to haunt him.
I'm very surprised
to see you here, Kenshin.
Did you finally decide
to visit this grave
after ten long years?
I had to come
eventually, Hiko.
And I see you managed
to find some nice flowers.
They're beautiful now,
but these flowers will
dry up and become dust,
just like my friend
beneath them.
All life has
a beginning and end,
and we can never change that.
No, I must
respect his privacy.
I don't want to
chase Aoshi away.
(thunder rumbling)
Oh!
As you can see, everything's
been fried to a crisp.
You were lucky
you weren't there.
Very few of us were
able to make it out
of that blasted inferno.
Hmm?
Huh?
He must have been
looking for Saito.
Oh, that's why he came here.
He wanted to find out
if Saito was still alive.
Fire was exploding everywhere.
I could barely
find my own way out,
let alone know what
happened to the others.
(rain falling)
I don't know what to think.
The fire made
many things unclear.
On the one hand,
it seemed hard to believe
that Saito could
actually be dead.
But it's even
more improbable
that he could
have survived.
You know what
Shishio would have said.
Huh?
"I was a winner
'cause I survived."
Come on, let's
get out of here.
Ever since the Meiji
government took over,
I've been wandering around
almost all of Japan,
except here.
It was too painful.
There were too
many people here
who knew me from the past,
and I didn't want to become
involved in a confrontation,
so I never attempted
to come back.
Tell me, is that
the only reason?
No, I'm afraid not.
The truth is that this
place also reminds me
of the people I killed.
Seems so senseless now.
The hardest part is that
none of them deserved to die.
And then...
Kenshin, let's go back
to Kyoto together.
Then everything
will be fine.
And then I was freed.
(moaning)
I was able to buy
these flowers.
That's something I couldn't
bring myself to do before.
Here, then go back to Kyoto
as soon as possible,
because I wouldn't want
to have to lend a hand
if some grudge
seeking enemy of yours
decides to pick a fight.
So long, Kenshin.
I guess I have to get
out of here, my friend.
See you the next
Obon Festival.
Till then,
rest easy.
I don't think Kenshin has
the desire to fight again,
but if he gets himself
into another situation
like the last time,
he'll give 100% of himself,
no matter what
his physical condition.
And that could
cost him his life.
How do you know?
He's not stupid,
why would he do anything
to hurt himself?
What can I do to
make her understand
the seriousness
of this situation?
He can't change now.
You're gonna have
to be strong
because Kenshin
needs your help.
It's important that
you give him a reason
to keep on living.
Your help alone will
ensure his survival.
Kori, I've seen
the way he looks at you.
There's something
special there.
You were the only one
that he said goodbye to
when he left Kyoto.
I can tell he cares
for you deeply,
even though he doesn't
always show it.
He'll listen to what
you have to say.
You're the only person
who can help protect him
from himself.
I want you to be
aware of how important
your position is
in this whole matter,
because I care
about him, too.
And I know that you care
about him even more,
so promise me that
you won't let him down.
All right, I've
finished my little speech
and I hope that
you understand.
I know you'll do
the right thing.
So what do you say?
Don't worry,
you can count on me.
Thank you so much, Megumi.
(sobbing)
There's no reason
to thank me.
I'm simply concerned
about Kenshin's
well-being, that's all.
I know.
Kori, are you going
to be all right?
You're crying again,
you are such a softie.
Oh, I'm sorry, Megumi.
How beautiful.
-Huh?
-Look!
Oh!
♪
I guess we'll never be able
to reach a final resolution.
Final resolution?
Are you talking about Saito?
Yes, we had our differences
and now we'll just
have to go beyond them.
Oh, I get it.
Sano didn't just
come here to find out
if Saito was dead or alive.
No, he wanted to find out
why they had differences
in the first place.
Instead of winning
the battle like he'd hoped,
he's just gonna have to
forget about it and move on.
Ah, he may have a point.
What purpose is there
in always being mad
and wanting to finish a fight?
That's what makes
Kenshin so great!
Ha ha!
Ah, if I don't let the little
things bother me so much,
Kenshin and the others
will respect me more.
♪
I had absolutely no idea
that this was
such a big city.
I thought you knew
your way around here!
Well, I hate to
tell you this, Sano,
but I think we're lost!
(growling)
Shut up!
We are not,
-you little twit!
-I know you are.
Come on.
Kori, this nitwit is lost.
Show him the way to
the nearest nuthouse!
Sano, you're the
one who got lost!
You couldn't
find your butt
-with both hands!
-Kori, I don't know
about you, but I think
we should get out of here.
As you can see,
I knew exactly where
I was going all along.
You got lucky,
dragon breath.
Hey, what are all
of you doing here?
Oh my...Kenshin!
Kenshin, you're not gonna
believe what happened.
This twerp got lost
-and I had to find him.
-Hey, don't listen to him,
he's the numbskull
that got lost, not me.
-Kenshin?
-Yeah?
Where were you all morning,
we were beginning
to get worried.
I just went to visit
the grave of a friend.
You mean you
actually went there?
Kenshin, this is cause
for celebration.
Why?
Because it means
you had a breakthrough.
-Oh.
-Hmm?
Yippie, he's human like us!
(laughing)
Hey, be careful.
Kenshin is still recovering.
We're not gonna hurt
him, my turn, Sano.
After all that's happened,
it's wonderful to see Kenshin
relaxing and having fun.
I just know everything
is going to work out great.
♪
Excuse me, Okina,
may I come in?
I wanted to
thank you for--huh?
Are you all right, Okina?
I'm fine, it's just that
I'm going to miss
all of you, that's all.
We're going
to miss you, too.
Thank you for all
that you've done for us.
My pleasure, Kenshin.
So how is Aoshi doing?
Well, you know how it is,
he's keeping to himself
and avoiding everyone.
I feel sorry for him.
Don't worry, Kenshin,
he'll be fine.
Huh?
Aoshi's been running
for an awfully long time
and needs a chance
to relax and meditate.
It's the best
thing he can do.
I'm afraid if he gets
too much rest,
he'll run off again,
but I guess that's
a chance we'll have to take.
Aoshi, what do you
think of this idea?
How about going out
sometime for sake?
So what do you think?
It will just be friends
getting together
for a drink.
I don't drink sake.
So probably not.
Oh, I'm sorry.
♪
But I do drink tea.
How about a tea ceremony?
That's great!
Oh, boy!
♪
Thanks for coming
to say goodbye to us, Misao.
I wanted to because I'm
really going to miss you all.
We'll miss you, too,
and be sure to tell Okina
how much we appreciated
his hospitality.
Sure, Kori.
Have a real nice trip, okay?
Guess what?
Sano's afraid
to ride the train!
Hey, I'm not afraid.
I just don't get
how this big teapot's
supposed to run itself.
Misao, take
good care of Aoshi.
Try to put a big
smile on his face.
I'll sure try.
(whistle blowing)
Come back and visit
us soon, okay?
Next time we see each other,
we can really have some fun.
And you're welcome
to visit us as well, Misao.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Bye!
Okay, we'll see you then.
You're all right for a girl.
And you're not bad
for a boy, either.
Take care, now.
Everything's gonna be
a lot better from now on.
♪
I know it will,
thanks a lot.
♪
See you later, Misao.
We'll look forward
to having you visit us.
Bye-bye,
you have a good trip
and remember,
don't forget to write.
We'll see each other real
soon, I promise, bye-bye!
Say goodbye to
everyone else for us!
♪
Bye, you guys!
Okina will be worried.
I'd better go back now.
I think your
pals are concerned.
Shouldn't you
tell them you're okay
before they worry
themselves sick?
What's the big deal?
You all fought together
to defeat Shishio.
Shishio needed
to be eliminated.
However, there are other
issues I have with Battousai
that need to be
resolved first.
What are you going
to do, Saito?
There will always be time
for another battle.
I just need to wait
until the right moment.
We were both
trained to fight,
and I'm sure we'll
meet again someday.
Hopefully, we'll face
each other as enemies,
but that will depend
entirely on the circumstances.
That would be a very
fortunate thing for me.
I'll be able to get back
at Battousai once and for all.
♪
Well, I'm sorry to say this,
but it's going to be very
quiet around here, Omasu.
They were such nice
people to have around.
Yes, they were lots
of fun, weren't they?
They were a great
group of youngsters,
hot-tempered at times,
but really very sweet.
♪
Oh, I know that I'm
going to really miss them.
♪
(train chugging)
I'm really looking
forward to going home.
Yes, so many things have
happened since we left.
♪
Well, I wish him luck.
Sano, I thought you'd
never let go of my hand
on that train ride.
Well, I just don't trust
those newfangled
contraptions.
By the way,
I'm gettin' hungry,
what's there to eat?
I wrote to Dr. Gensai
that we were going
to be arriving today.
Knowing him, I'm sure he's
preparing something special.
That's great,
because I'm starving!
It's been such a long time
since we've walked
together like this, Kenshin.
Kenshin?
Huh?
Is anything wrong?
Tell me, please.
It feels sort
of strange, Kori.
When I left, I was
a wanderer that was afraid
the demon within me
would do some harm.
I didn't want to put
any of you in danger,
so I tried to avoid it.
But I've changed.
Coming back to this place
puts everything
in perspective.
In my heart, it feels
right to be here.
Kenshin, do you remember
when we first came here?
Huh?
I'll never forget it.
This is the place
where you first said
goodbye to me, remember?
I was afraid to tell him
that I wanted him in my life,
he wouldn't have understood.
But after all
we've gone through,
I think he's ready.
Kenshin?
This is your home
from now on.
♪
You'll always
have a place here,
no matter what happens.
♪
Kenshin, welcome home.
There's a certainty when you
know that something's right.
I felt it when
I first met Kenshin.
I knew that there
was goodness in him.
But he needed to find
that out for himself.
Our family has a
new permanent member,
if he decides to stay.
For now, we'll
just have to see.
But I feel optimistic.
Kenshin and I have
something special
that no one
will ever take away.
At last, I have a home.
♪
(singing in foreign language)