♪
Strange occurrences
and the appearance
of a mysterious stranger have
left unanswered questions.
Two families from
the distant past
hold the future
in their hands.
Thanks, Mr. Saeke.
The strongest family
is still to be determined.
It will be the one
that can control the
power of feng shui.
Hey, we're being attacked!
(Tae whimpering)
(yelling)
Watch out!
♪
(yells)
Kenshin!
Did they hurt you?
Who are you?
♪
I'm here...
(breathing heavily)
♪
to save you from
being destroyed.
I don't believe it.
A star.
♪
What do you
mean "save us"?
-Huh?
Kamachakijan,
you have no power here.
I want you to
leave this place.
Now!
♪
Just where did
you come from?
They call me Jinpu.
I'm a descendant
of the wind family.
My family defeated
the water family
in a struggle for power.
What power?
It's feng shui.
Mm-hmm.
They've come
back to try again.
We have his company's
financial records.
What about his
other businesses?
We need time.
Get it to me
in two hours.
I want that information
as soon as possible, got it?
Yes, sir.
(growls)
There was
another incident.
What incident is that?
I received a strange report
about a beef pot restaurant
that burned the other day.
What of it?
A man by the name
of Saeke came by there
and pressured the woman who
owned the place to move out.
That rubbish again?
I'm not going to waste
my time on this bull.
Feng shui is a
bunch of nonsense,
but I do think it's odd that
whenever something happens
that Saeke character
is involved.
He's starting to
become a public nuisance.
But I don't think it's
something we can just ignore.
Fine, then
you deal with it!
As of now, I'm putting
you in charge of the case.
Do what you want.
Thanks, I truly
appreciate that.
Hmm,
you're welcome.
Just what I need.
As if I don't have
enough problems already.
Jinpu, there are so many
questions I want to ask you,
but first, what made
you decide to help us?
This fight has
nothing to do with you
and I'm sick and tired
of seeing people die.
Why bother?
We're perfectly capable
of defending ourselves.
You make it sound like we're
a bunch of helpless oafs.
It's too much for you
to even comprehend.
Well, why not?
Excuse me.
I'm glad to catch
everybody here.
I wanted to talk with you
about something very important.
Would anyone care
for some watermelon?
-I do!
-Same here!
Whoo, yeah!
You want to know
something about Mr. Saeke?
Hmm.
He began doing
business immediately
after the fall of
the Tokugawa era.
It made him very
rich and successful.
I was told that his company's
involved in several ventures.
That's right.
He's been working on
a railroad this month.
Thanks, pal.
What town is it in?
It's over in Musashino,
not far from here.
Musashino?
Have a slice, Chief.
Thanks, I will.
Please go ahead with
your conversation.
Jinpu, what was the
cause of the disagreement
that made the
two families fight?
A very long time ago our two
families lived in harmony.
Then, one day a feud
threatened to end that peace.
If the battle
ended so long ago,
what made the water family come
back and continue to fight?
But before I tell
you all about it,
I have something
to show you.
Huh?
♪
The city.
Yeah, I can see
Tae's restaurant.
And right there
is the Kamiya dojo.
Hey, wait, how come
they're connected
by that weird star shape?
Each point
represents a spot
where magic jin
have been placed
to protect the
energy force.
The person who originally
designed the plan
was Iaso Tokugawa.
-Tokugawa?
At the very beginning
of his reign,
Tokugawa secretly
send up the mahojin
in order to protect the city
of Ito from possible disaster.
♪
He would build a
series of three shrines.
The purpose was to
prevent any poisonous air
from entering each
triangular shaped area.
This maintained the
cleanliness of the ki.
♪
He then put a triangle
on top of another triangle.
To create a five
point star shape.
This doubled
the protection.
Mountains, rivers and the
ocean were also utilized
to control the flow
of energy into the city.
In the east, there
is the Sumida river.
In the west,
is the Tokaido Road.
The south is
marked by Ito Bay.
The north is Mount Fuji.
We call these
points igunojin.
Igu stands for
eternity, doesn't it, Jinpu?
Uh-huh.
The people who
built this city
and designed its
defense were my ancestors.
It was a very complicated task
to perfect the arrangement.
The families fought.
The water family wanted
to build it's own strategy,
what we call, jin,
but our jin wasn't
compatible with theirs.
A battle raged for the control
of ki, or energy flow.
Many people were killed and
property was destroyed.
Our family eventually won
and we completed the design.
The water family was extremely
angry that they lost
and vowed to come back
to this land someday
and complete their jin.
They disappeared from sight
and were never
heard from again,
until just recently.
That must have been when
these incidents happened.
Yes, you're
absolutely right.
What happened at the
restaurant and the dojo
was part of the
water family's plan
to destroy our
jin structure.
I bet they're
planning to connect
a brand new
jin formation.
Hey, hold on
for a minute.
If they complete this jin,
what'll happen
to all the people
who live and work here?
Answer me that!
Everybody here
will be destroyed.
You're kidding me right?
Just for some jin?
Yeah, how come, Jinpu?
The power of ki is awesome.
We believe that our
purpose is to maintain
and control the ki so that
it always remains stable.
The water family wants
to use it to control power.
That's very dangerous,
because they'll manipulate it
to suit themselves,
disturbing the harmony.
Although it is good,
jin can also be
a double edged sword
that is capable
of mass destruction
if it is used unwisely.
For example, when
China became involved
in that awful opium war,
the use of
drugs was widespread.
England invaded the country,
completely decimating it.
Leaving a horrible trail
of blood in its wake.
♪
Events like this were just a
consequence of something else.
This is what happened.
Apparently the Chinese
couldn't control the flow of ki
and it backfired.
If water makes a change, the
same thing will happen here.
We must guard against this,
but I have to confess
that it's impossible for me
to do it alone.
Please everyone.
For the sake of this country,
I need you to help me.
(clock ticking)
(sighs)
I'm telling you, sir,
we don't have time to wait.
We have to set up
a special force
to investigate this
before it gets any worse.
Oh, really?
And who do you think is
going to believe that report?
Sir, if you have any
doubts on my report,
than I suggest
that we go and talk
with the ministry
of the army.
I'm convinced, alright.
I'll set up a meeting.
Ah, well now, let me take you
to see a man named Mr. Jinpu.
He knows what it's about.
You'd really
make me do that?
Sir.
Yes?
We've just learned
that the Saeke company
is building a railroad near
the town of Musashino.
It's been under construction
for some time we believe.
A railroad?
Yes, sir.
We think that there
was fraud involved
to make the government actively
participate in the project.
Ha!
I thought this man's
primary business
was in real estate
and shipping.
That is strange.
This could be an
important problem.
Come on!
What now?
We can't waste
any more time
trying to figure
out something
we know nothing about.
Let's visit the Kamiya
dojo immediately.
Alright,
I'll go if I have to.
(metal scraping)
A private company is
building its own railroad?
Yes, do you
think it's possible?
We imported engineers
from England to teach us
how to operate these trains,
so it seems odd to me.
It would be too
hard to pull off.
Of course, there
is the possibility
they got a little
help from China.
What do you mean?
I've been told
that England
is building
railroads all over China.
That could be your
answer right there.
Could be.
♪
You think
that those things
will make the well
water go back to normal?
No, I'm afraid they won't.
The flow of ki is very strong
underneath the ground.
Once it's disturbed it needs
a higher level of treatment.
You'll have to find
the cause to stop it.
Tell me something, Jinpu.
Certainly, Kenshin.
What is it?
What made the
water family return
after such a long
stretch of time?
The Tokugawa
era has ended.
Our new government
is exhausted
from last year's seinen war
and is trying to rebuild.
It's a perfect time for
them to rearrange the jin.
That's why
they've come back.
The government
that's taken power
is unaware of the magnitude
of our contribution.
You mean, they don't know
anything about feng shui, Jinpu?
Very little.
They believe it's just
a superstitious idea.
The truth is
both families
put their lives
into feng shui
and many of us
lost loved ones
because of our belief.
I was born
into this life.
It's a part of me
and I will continue
to practice its methods.
I will never give up.
Even if I am the
only one left to survive.
In these modern times,
people probably don't
think they need
anything like feng shui.
Yes, but they're wrong.
They need it
more than ever.
A sword is not used
just to kill people.
It can be used
to save people.
Isn't that right?
Mm-hmm.
♪
(men shouting)
Speed it up!
You men are too slow!
We can't move any faster
than we're going.
The men are wiped out.
They work far
too many hours.
Well, you'd better
get more men then.
We have a
schedule to meet
and we're going to
meet it, you hear?
I need two more men
over here to help.
Huh?
♪
What's this?
-Hey!
-Huh?
This is off-limits, now
move away from the fence.
Don't worry,
I'm not a bad guy.
I just want some work.
I was surveying
all the options.
Are there any
jobs available?
Oh, I thought you
were spying on the company.
The information's
right over there.
Perfect.
What's the deal?
How come they're building
a railroad station
in such a secluded place?
Oh, beats me.
I don't know what those
big shots are thinking.
The weird thing is, they haven't
even laid down any tracks.
All they're doing
is digging tunnels.
Tunnels, huh?
Doesn't sound like much
of a railroad to me.
I wanna know more
about this Mr. Saeke.
(thunder rumbles)
(rain pouring)
Hello everyone,
I'm home.
Well, it's about time!
Do you know
where Kenshin went?
To the dojo.
He wanted some peace and
quiet so that he could think.
He bought into everything that
feng shui man had told him.
Sometimes he's so naive,
it makes me puke.
I'm tired.
I know.
You'd better get
your beauty sleep.
Would you let me go?
I don't see the
point of this anyway.
This is a waste of my time.
I want to go back.
It's extremely important
that you meet this man, sir.
He's a quack!
You men must be sopping
wet from the rain.
Why did you come
here on a night like this?
I'm sorry to disturb
you so late this evening,
but I wanted
Captain Koachi to hear
Jinpu's story for himself.
(growls)
Uh-huh.
Let's make this short, Jinpu.
Or whatever your
name happens to be.
Just excuse him.
Please, Mr. Jinpu.
If you don't mind, tell
Captain Koachi the same story
you told me yesterday.
Does he know
about Mr. Saeke
and how he's
been conning people
into selling
their businesses?
What?
Did you tell him
all about that?
Huh?
I believe that
there's a connection
between Saeke's
company and a plan
to overthrow the government
by disrupting its jin.
Right!
You expect me to
believe this crap?
The man is a menace.
Huh?
I don't often find myself
helping the police,
but this time the
police chief is right.
He's supposedly building
a private railroad,
but it looks like
he's using it
to camouflage
something else.
We just received some
information about that.
So, who are you, anyway?
That's Tsunan,
he's my friend.
What else
do you know?
I did some
investigating of my own.
He's digging a big
tunnel that I'm convinced
he's got some
big plans for.
What did you just say?
He's building a what?
Take a look at this.
What a strange
looking map.
Why does it have all those
squiggly lines on it?
There's a spring where
the rumayagu flows freely
back to the town
of Musashino.
That makes the town
an important starting point
to manipulate the ki
and create a formation.
If Saeke builds
a tunnel there,
he will be able
to control the ki
from the spring
and its strength.
He can send it
straight into the city.
If that happens, the jin
that is protecting this area
will be crushed and everyone
living here will die.
(gasps)
-Everyone?
-Hey, wait.
How are you
going to prove that?
Tell me how this man
became a feng shui master.
From what I understand,
Mr. Saeke originally came
to this country from China,
and the feng shui expert that
appeared at the restaurant
used a flame technique.
In feng shui, the only
method that utilizes flames
is a technique out of China.
Tang feng shui.
Are you sure
about that?
Are you saying that
Saeke is collaborating
with the Chinese
in some way?
The name Yunoshin Saeke
is not his real name.
It's an alias he made up
when he came to Japan.
I believe his
real name is Yusui.
That's all I know
about him so far.
That name has an
ending that is similar
to all the other names
in the water clan.
Saeke must be a direct
descendant of that family.
What?
It's true.
After our families battled 270
years ago, they fled to China.
It was there that
they became familiar
with the Tang
feng shui method.
Koachi, you shouldn't
underestimate feng shui.
It was a technique practiced in
the Ming and the Tang dynasties.
In fact, it was practiced
even earlier than that.
When it is
practiced incorrectly,
it's a double edged sword
that can cause great harm.
I understand, sir.
I think we have more than
enough proof, don't you?
Well?
Well, I think so.
There have been too
many coincidences
that Mr. Saeke has been
directly involved with.
I'll help you.
(sighs)
Yes, I believe
it's a good cause,
so count me
in, Mr.Jinpu.
(gasps)
That's wonderful.
This bad habit of yours
is getting way out of hand.
We have no choice
in the matter, Sano,
I've thought about it.
Right now, Mr. Saeke
is after the restaurant
and the Kamiya dojo.
It would be awful if we
were to lose both of them.
Hmm.
There's no way
I'll do it.
Huh?
This is stupid.
Forget about feng shui.
It's a bunch of bunk
if you ask me.
Hmm?
(wind howling)
Who the hell
are those guys?
What do they want?
That guy in the center
looks like the one
who burned up
the restaurant.
(laughing)
That's right.
I head the water family.
My name is Reisui.
So, we have come back.
What's your purpose for
returning to Japan?
To get our ki back.
It won't be long until
we accomplish that goal.
And nothing is going to
stop us this time, my friend.
We've got you
where we want you.
Oh, yeah?
Take this!
How about that?
Had enough,
sweetheart?
Want more?
Aim for their side.
That's where their ki
is most vulnerable.
Shut up.
I'll use the modern way.
I'll beat 'em up.
Wow.
Their sides are their
weak spots, Sano.
Yeah, I can see that.
(grunting)
(growls)
Keep your eyes
closed, Kenshin,
and don't look
at that stick.
Yamato feng shui,
enter the labyrinth.
Lose yourself in
the glowing light.
Nay, kneel.
Satsu!
(energy pulsing)
This is a
shijo in Kyoto.
How did I get transported
back to this battle scene?
Battosai.
Battosai,
the slasher.
You took our
lives, Battosai.
It's your turn to die a
horrible death like we did.
(ghosts yelling)
Kenshin, get a
hold of yourself.
You have to
snap out of it.
(breathing heavily)
(grunting)
(yells)
(groans)
Huh?
Kaoru!
Forget about her.
Poison air is
entering her blood.
She's halfway
to her death.
No!
(yells)
You haven't heard
the last of us.
Oh, Kaoru!
Come on, Kaoru, you've
gotta survive this thing.
It's all my fault.
Once they've wounded her, it
can't be undone by anyone.
I'm afraid
she's been poisoned.
(laughing evilly)
I destroyed
all five jin.
That will stop
the flow of ki.
Now, I can do
whatever I want.
(laughing)
I don't need the
restaurant or the dojo.
Those things are
insignificant to me now.
I'm now free to
place the jin
anywhere that
suits my needs.
I will change the
flow of ki forever.
I will lead all Japan.
(wind whistling)
(electricity crackling)
♪
(whimpering)
Tell me, will she
make it or not?
I want to know!
Well, we can try
treating the wound,
but it might not help.
Poison air has
entered her blood stream
and it doesn't
look good for her.
Huh?
(Yoshi groaning)
I should've been there.
I can't believe that
she might not get better
and it's all because
I went to sleep.
Oh, Kaoru.
Himura.
Look, it's Mr. Yamagata.
The Ministry
of Construction.
It's all gone.
It just disappeared.
And how could that happen?
It's about to begin.
And we will have to
fight them in Nagunojn.
This is called a battle
of complete destruction.
Well, we're ready.
(wind chime tinkles)
♪