♪
Misao had learned
the real story
of Shogo's childhood.
She explained to us
the terrible tragedy
that had taken place
in Shimabara all those
years ago.
Young Shogo had witnessed
his mother's murder and all
his Christian friends crucified
by men who hated Christians.
Even though he had
escaped with his life,
he vowed then and there
to take his revenge on
the Japanese authorities
for allowing this massacre.
Even as we learned
the secret story
of Shogo's past,
we discovered Santo
having what appears to be
a clandestine meeting
with an army of men.
Who are they and
what are they up to?
There's no telling what
will happen next to all of us.
♪
Lady Magdalia,
it looks as though
you've run out of time.
You are scum!
Huh?
(gasping)
♪
What are your wishes, Sir Kaiou?
Kill them, I want Lady Magdalia
and her pesky friends to die.
Right.
♪
(grunting)
(gasping)
Oh no!
♪
Who...
are you?
I am Ramon.
Kaiou ordered me to eliminate
anyone who gets in the way
of our plans.
Too bad for you.
It sounds like Kaiou's
running the show
instead of Shogo.
But why does he want
to get an army involved
and whose army
is it anyway?
You'll never know that!
♪
Those kunai spears
should do the trick!
What?
Huh?
♪
No, don't!
He's gonna fall!
♪
I-I can't.
Nice move!
Hey.
(rumbling)
Huh?
It's an earthquake!
I don't think so.
Well then, what is it?
It feels more like
an underground cave-in.
It feels pretty close
to where Sano and I
split up, we'd better hurry.
(grunting)
Sayo, are you okay?
I think so.
And Shozo?
Oh, my gosh, he's...
he's pinned under that rock!
He shielded you, Sayo,
but now he's half-buried.
♪
Shozo, are you hurt?
It's all right, I'm here.
Lady Magdalia, are
you all right, milady?
Please answer.
Put my mind to rest.
Yes, thanks to
your help, I'm fine.
♪
Shozo, even as a child,
you were always willing
to help others, even at
great personal sacrifice.
That's what you taught:
the life of a Christian
is based upon giving service
to God's will and God's people,
no matter what the price
is to us individually.
You've learned well,
but I've never seen someone
so willing to put
God's word into practice.
(sobbing)
♪
Don't cry, Lady Magdalia.
Don't waste your tears on me.
And besides, I'm not
going to die anytime soon.
I have too much left to do,
so don't worry about me.
We will help you, Shozo.
There's gotta be
a way to rescue him.
Huh?
♪
I'm not a Christian,
Lady Magdalia,
but Shozo saved my life
and I wanna save him.
♪
I can't believe
this is happening.
Lady Magdalia's
gonna save me again.
(grunting)
♪
It's moving!
Don't stop, keep pushing!
That's it!
It's almost off!
(grunting)
♪
(coughing)
Lady Magdalia!
It must be the dust
that's making you cough
so badly.
Look there, Shozo's free!
Dust isn't what's
making her cough.
Lady Magdalia is ill
and yet, she risked
making herself worse
just to help me.
(coughing)
It was God that set you free.
You must do us a favor, Shozo.
You must tell my
brother about Kaiou
before he kills many people.
As you wish, milady,
but I can't just leave
you here all alone.
Go tell Shogo
about Kaiou's plans.
I'll be fine.
♪
It's one of Kaiou's men!
You get out of here!
Lady Magdalia, what are
you still doing alive?
Looks like I'll
have to bury you
and your gutless friends.
Not while I'm here!
Wait, Shozo, you can't beat him
after what you
just went through!
But you could go
and tell Shogo.
He has to know all
about Kaiou's evil plans.
I give you my word,
I will protect Lady Magdalia
to the death.
Take these with you.
They are highly explosive
when you drop them.
A friend got them
for me in China.
You might need them.
Take them, Shozo,
and go quickly!
I trust you.
I will go and tell Shogo
and I will succeed
with God's help.
Hey, bald boy.
Whaddaya say we have
a real fight to the death?
(growling)
♪
You stay here while I
take care of this guy.
Great, I finally get a chance
to show off to Lady Magdalia.
♪
You're gonna tell me something
or I'll see you suffer!
♪
I'd say you're the one
that's gonna suffer!
I don't think so, cueball!
♪
Now die!
Now I wanna know,
just where is that medallion?
♪
Tell me!
Mr. Santo has got it.
Santo's got it!
Ha!
(grunting)
(gasps)
Lady Magdalia!
It can't be!
You've finally come to.
(groaning)
♪
I guess what Shozo
said earlier was right.
You really are very
sick, aren't you?
That's right.
I know soon I'll
be leaving this Earth.
(gasps)
Unless God grants me a miracle,
I'll soon be with
Him in His kingdom.
(coughs)
Don't joke about death!
You probably just have
a very bad cold or something.
Besides, you know I
don't believe in God.
You think this God of yours
has the ability to control
what happens to us?
Only a human can save
another human's life.
This whole concept you have,
that some divine entity
is helping you survive
on Earth is strictly hogwash.
I'll tell you what I believe in:
friendship.
I have real friends
that help me survive.
Kenshin, Kori, Yoshi.
When things get really tough,
they are always there for me.
They can't make miracles happen,
but I trust them.
I know that they'd
do whatever they could
to help me no matter what.
I'm doing my best to save you.
I'm just asking you
to believe in me, please?
♪
(growling)
(gasping)
♪
Hey, Yoshi!
It's your friend,
just like you said!
Sano, I'd say you
owe me big-time!
Hey, Sano!
I'm sure glad to hear
you're still in one piece,
my friend.
Kenshin, what's the matter?
Can't you see anything?
I've lost my sight temporarily.
But he still fights
like good old Kenshin.
Yeah, he's got
a little vision problem,
but it hasn't cramped
his style in the least.
Oh, my, take a look
at Lady Magdalia!
♪
Kaiou is going to betray Shogo.
Kaiou plans on ruling Japan
by murdering Shogo and stealing
all of his followers
with this Book of Prophecy
he's created.
By sending the army
to kill Shogo Amakusa,
Kaiou can tell his followers
that he died like a martyr
and take over Shogo's position
as leader of the movement.
Kaiou must have reported
to Nagasaki's governor
that a riot was about
to occur in Shimabara.
That's how he got
the army there.
So, Kaiou is using
the army to do his bidding.
I'd bet in his book,
he'll say that Shogo
will be killed
by the government.
He'll use the anger
Shogo's followers feel
towards the authorities
to steamroll his way
into becoming
the ruler of Japan!
With 10,000 followers
behind him, he'll take
over in no time.
How are we gonna stand a chance
of stopping this megalomaniac?
Well, whatever it takes
to stop this fiend,
we have to do it or
Japan will be destroyed!
(coughing)
I really wish I could stop him.
Shogo went to Holy Hill.
All the villagers
went with him.
If the army--
(coughing)
That sounds like tuberculosis.
No, it can't be that!
I still think it would
be wise to have Dr. Elsten
examine her just in case.
That's right!
That Dutch guy's a doctor!
I'd forgotten all about that.
Sano, leave right now!
You really mean it?
♪
And when you see Dr. Elsten,
don't forget to tell him
about the situation
regarding Shogo and the army!
Maybe Dr. Elsten can stop
the army from attacking Shogo
and his people, and explain
to him Kaiou's plans!
I guess we'd
better get moving.
You mean to Holy Hill?
We can't allow all those poor,
innocent villagers
to be massacred.
You're right about that.
We've got to talk Shogo Amakusa
out of this thing.
♪
Sir!
Steady, Trigger!
The 12th Infantry is in
position and ready, sir!
It is certainly
going to be a hot day.
♪
It certainly is a hot day.
It appears that the trip
across the water from Shimabara
has made your poor little
sister sick, Shogo.
Uncle Hyouei, I want
to ask you something.
I want you to teach me
Hiten Mitsurugi style, please?
I want to learn
to be the greatest,
the best.
I want to be a god
when it comes
to swordsmanship.
Just like God,
I want to save people
and I want to protect
my sister, Sayo.
We lost so many
good Christian friends
on the Holy Hill on Shimabara.
Most of all, I want
to punish those people
who killed my parents
in cold blood.
I am so proud to hear
you say that, Shogo.
I have always felt
that it was truly
my destiny to teach you.
I feel like you have been
chosen specifically by God.
I will teach you
the Hiten Mitsurugi sword style.
You can't use
that style to kill.
Why?
Hiten Mitsurugi
is a style used
to defend people,
it's not used to attack
or kill unless you
have no other choice.
You must lose your hatred,
otherwise you will never
attain true Hiten
Mitsurugi greatness.
Becoming God is impossible,
but at least you'll be able
to protect Sayo.
You must understand
this sword style
is to help people.
It was not created
to quench your thirst
for revenge.
(thunder)
No matter what you say, Uncle,
it is my destiny.
I know I will become a god.
(thunder)
"Becoming God
is impossible, Shogo,
but at least you'll
be able to protect Sayo...
protect Sayo."
I saw mother and
father in my dream.
I'll be joining
them very soon now.
I can't wait--
we'll be together again.
Sayo.
♪
It's time for you to say
goodbye to Shimabara,
Sir Kaiou.
(chuckles)
When you return, you'll
be our country's leader
with hundreds of thousands
of faithful followers,
all thanks to
your brilliant plan.
Soon, the army
surrounding Holy Hill
will attack
and Shogo Amakusa
and 88 of his followers
will be shot to death!
Yes, 88 of them!
It's a good number
and, more importantly,
it matches the number
that I have featured
in my book that prophesizes
Shogo's untimely death.
I'm only sorry I can't see
that child of God squeal
like a pig as he dies!
(chuckles)
We'd better go, Sir Kaiou.
The steamship is waiting
for us offshore.
Quite.
Kaiou!
Hey, it's Shozo!
You're lucky I've been
taught to be a Christian
or I'd tear you apart
with my bare hands!
You're making me regret
that I have sworn never
to kill another human being!
God grant me the
strength to not kill you!
I just love a good animal story,
even if it is
from Amakusa's dog!
That's it!
Die!
♪
I've heard, "Let
sleeping dogs lie,"
but this runt had to die!
Well, it was my pleasure
to give you a first class
ticket to the Resurrection.
(chuckling)
I feel like King of the World!
(cackling)
♪
Forgive me, Lady Magdalia.
I beg of you, forgive
me for what I do.
Let's go.
Huh?
♪
(explosion)
Sir Shogo, we just
heard an explosion!
The army has us surrounded!
(gasps)
♪
Captain, all our troops await
your order to attack, sir.
♪
Mm-hmm.
From what I can make out,
Holy Hill is already surrounded.
Does that mean
the attack's gonna start?
Kenshin, what should we do?
We must somehow stop them.
♪
Sayo, as much as
I care about you,
I will not let you die.
You must live.
I made a solemn vow to Shozo
and to myself to protect you,
no matter what the cost.
♪