♪
(singing in foreign language)
(birdsong)
It's wonderful
to be back home.
Smell the air.
♪
And pretty soon,
it'll be white again.
Nothing's changed here.
Everything's the same.
Unbelievable.
It's hard to believe
that our very own Kenshin
just won a battle in which
our country's fate
hung in the balance.
Mm-hmm.
Now let's see how it looks.
-Wow!
-It looks better.
-You're a good scrubber.
-Great, just two more
and we'll be all done.
So I got to admit,
all this work is
making me hungry.
So what's for lunch,
lobster, red snapper,
hey, I don't mind if all
you got is pickled eel.
-Heh!
-Ugh!
Shame on you.
You're the laziest
bum I've ever seen
and the fact that you
think you're entitled
to anything more than a kick
in the butt is unbelievable.
You need to go on
another long trip
and pound some rocks
with your fists again.
Maybe you're the one
that needs a little pounding!
As a fighter,
you're so lame
you couldn't beat
an egg with a fork.
You've gone too far!
-Hey!
-And I've had it!
Stop it right now!
If you two ever want to
get any food from me again,
you'd better follow me.
Sano, it's been almost a year
since you put
this hole in the wall.
And since you're responsible
for creating this eyesore,
I'm sure you can understand
why I want you to fix it.
Hey now, it wasn't me
who made that hole, Kori,
that was Saito's
doing, I tell ya.
You will fix it, now!
Ooh, ouch-a, she got ya.
And Yoshi, you need to
earn your keep as well.
That hole let
a lot of dirt in here
and I need you
to clean it up.
I want you to mop and scrub
the floor ten times today.
Ten times, but I--
Miss Kori, I finished the
laundry and watering the garden,
is there anything else?
Thanks, follow me, Kenshin.
(papers rustling)
There's something in here
that can help all of us.
There you go.
This is a very
thin bamboo sword.
It's for fishing.
Fishing?
It's a fishing pole.
You see, we spent all our
money trying to find you,
so we have no food money.
So I was hoping
you'd take that pole
and go fishing so we might
have something for dinner.
(grumbling)
Hey, Kenshin, get out there
and catch us a bunch of fish.
Go for it, we'll be working,
so by the time you get back
here, we'll be starving!
And you know how cranky
I get when I don't eat!
-Wish us luck.
-Bye-bye.
Hope you catch some fish.
Now we should get started.
Oh!
♪
June 22nd.
The calendar on the wall
shows that time stopped here
almost a year ago.
I'll never be able
to forget the day
that the whole
world stopped for me.
♪
I remember what he said
when he was leaving,
and how it made me feel.
I'll never forget that
warm early summer night.
It was the first
day in my life
that I felt like a woman.
♪
(stream babbling)
This looks like a good spot.
Hmm, uh, uh.
That'll work.
(water babbling)
(birdsong)
Kenshin, when are
you gonna catch a whale?
A fish would do.
You know, I think
I got a bite.
-Huh!
Oh.
Look, it's our
fisherman friend.
He always catches
a lot of fish.
Mister, will you
teach us how to fish?
We're coming to see you.
♪
Hey, kid, you didn't
ask for permission
to cross our bridge.
Yeah, that's gonna
cost you some money.
We know your dad's rich
so you better hand it over.
Please, somebody,
anybody, help me.
Huh?
(menacing laughter)
Well, we did warn you, kid.
(groaning)
What the hell
happened to him?
Maybe bad sushi.
Hey, where's my dagger?
It just vanished
into thin air.
(groaning)
♪
Who is this guy?
What an exhibition
of precision and speed.
He moves with
the power of a master,
the stealth of a ninja.
Who is he?
(metal whizzing)
(splash)
If I didn't know better,
I'd say there's
a spirit around here.
It must be a ghost
of the river.
You thugs get away
from my son!
So you like
bullying my son, huh?
Well, it's your turn.
Take this.
(punch)
(water gurgling)
I bet you won't
be trying that again.
Yeah, jerk.
(footsteps)
(gasping)
They pushed down our friend,
and now he's dead!
Let your grief
fly away, children.
-Huh?
-Wow!
I promised you
these last time.
Wow, thank you, mister.
You could have sat
at that spot for ten years
and not caught a fish.
(water babbling)
I can help.
I know a much
better fishing spot.
♪
-There.
-Oh.
(giggling)
♪
We've been given
a perfect day for fishing.
♪
I feel like you have
so much good in your heart.
I know it's not my business,
but when did you quit
being a slasher?
You know, I've
met quite a few
of the new
generation of slashers,
but none of them
were as humble and kind
as I get the feeling you are.
I watched how you dealt with
those thugs on the bridge.
You used your
skills so subtly.
Here we sit, two swordsmen
who've lost their fangs.
Fate has been
good to both of us.
It's allowed us
to live long enough
to have this
opportunity to meet.
I feel like you have
a story I should hear.
Hmm.
Have you ever been here
in the summer at night?
This whole place
is filled with fireflies.
That's why this place
used to be called
Wishing Firefly Bend.
Wishing Firefly?
Yes, that's what they
called it a long time ago.
What I'm about to tell
you happened many years
before the Edo era had ended.
It's a story that will
certainly interest you.
And it's my story to tell.
Match!
I've never seen
such technique.
Yeah, he's got all that
talent and he's only 16.
Hey, Ryunosuke,
congratulations!
It was amazing
the way you won that match.
That guy had a lot more
experience than you,
but you still won.
I don't think there's
a swordsman in all of Edo
that's better than you.
I heard this rumor--
I was wondering,
were you really asked
to do a demonstration
in front of the Shogun?
Yes, and I declined.
It's silly.
You did what?
Are you crazy?
Why'd you do that?
I'm just not
really satisfied
with my sword fighting
skills yet.
I can't tell how
good a fighter I am
from these sparring matches.
There's really only
one way to find out
if I'm as good
as you say I am.
And it's not
with a bamboo sword.
I want to get better,
and the only way
to achieve that
is the way of the Samurai.
To truly put yourself
in harms way.
You attain real strength
only by experiencing danger.
But you are strong,
I don't understand.
Well, you can never
be too strong.
I just want to achieve
absolute strength.
♪
Do you know that
girl over there?
That's my sister Kinu,
I've introduced
you to her five times.
Kinu, say hi.
Ah, come on,
don't get shy now.
Hey, where are you going?
♪
For a guy that's so sharp,
you sure don't see
what's around you.
What?
You ever heard of
Wishing Firefly Bend?
It's this place on the river,
that legend has it,
if you go there and pray
every day for a year
for something to happen,
the fireflies
make your wish come true
when they arrive
in early summer.
Firefly Bend?
That's the place.
My sister has been
going there for two months
to try and get the fireflies
to let you know how
she feels about you.
Kinu's pretty shy
when it comes to guys.
But I guess she must
like you a whole lot.
Huh?
Not long after that,
fate decided that
my world should change.
From sunny days
to the cold, dark night,
the fates had heard me.
I never had to pray
to the fireflies.
But as a wise
philosopher said,
"Be careful
what you wish for."
My life changed that
dark, stormy night,
and it was just a matter
of being somewhere
when something happened.
(thunder cracking)
Get him, stop him!
He just robbed us!
♪
So you think you can get away
with dishonoring our house
by taking what
is rightfully ours?
You must die for your crime!
♪
Arrgh!
Ugh!
♪
(whinnying)
This ninja wasn't
just some petty thief,
he was truly a ninja
who meted out death
with the sword of thunder god.
I was amazed at what I saw
in the faces of the dead men.
All of them had restful
expressions on their faces.
It was obvious
they had died so quickly
that they never
knew what hit them.
And it scared me.
There's one still alive!
♪
Argh!
(sword slashing)
♪
That night was the first
time I killed a man.
♪
I had to explain
a difficult decision.
That's not possible.
You would never do
anything like that.
I know you,
I know your heart,
and you are not a killer.
But I could develop
a taste for blood.
If I'm ever going
to be a great swordsman,
death is certainly
part of the journey.
It's kill or be killed.
You stop this talk.
Listen, I care about
what happens to you,
so don't go!
Enough.
Ryunosuke, I beg of you, stay.
If you're really
going to kill again,
then I ask you
to please kill me first.
♪
(sobbing)
You could never
understand my dreams!
No!
Don't leave me!
♪
I left that day and
tried to forget Kinu.
I went on a rampage to
prove myself as a swordsman.
Soon after that,
death became a very
close associate of mine.
No matter how much I killed,
I never felt
satisfied with myself.
My heart was filled
with discontent.
The years dragged on and
I had no friends, no life,
and what I had chosen
for a life began to haunt me.
♪
I was no longer
living life,
I merely existed.
I was chasing
an impossible dream.
I didn't know it,
but I was trying to
relive that stormy night
when I'd been forced
to tap my savage power.
♪
No, this isn't it,
I haven't found it.
I was the heartless, faceless,
nameless messenger of death.
One day, 15 years
had passed me by.
Finally, after
21 years of wandering,
fate imposed itself once again
into my desolate existence.
Help, stop that thief!
He killed our son!
(horse galloping)
It's him!
Even after all that time,
I knew it was him!
The ninja that had
changed my life!
♪
I felt the same rage
that I had felt so long ago.
♪
(swords clanking)
When I saw him lying
there dead, I shuddered.
His face was etched
with the same serene look
of those men he had
killed on that rainy night
over 20 years ago.
And it was then I realized
there was no longer
a reason for me to kill.
I had finally
survived long enough
to achieve my sick dream.
I had become a monster,
just like him.
♪
(sobbing)
I woke up to a nightmare.
I was left with nothing
but guilt for
the youth I'd wasted
and the lives I'd taken.
(gasping)
Ah!
♪
N-n-n-no!
I can't take it!
How could I have thought
of life as so worthless?
I was so wrong!
Tell me why!
How could I?
Why did I give up
my life for this hell?
(gasping)
(crickets chirping)
Ryunosuke.
(water rushing)
♪
It's finally over.
Your long journey
to find your soul
has finally been completed.
I have waited such
a long time to hold you.
♪
I've been waiting
all these years.
♪
I knew I must return to home,
where my life had meaning
and there was someone
who loved me.
Greetings, I bet
you've come here
because you've heard about
Wishing Firefly Bend, right?
Hey, you're Shinpachi.
That's me, but, uh,
I don't recognize you.
Uh, you must have known
my sister Kinu.
She waited her whole life
for a man who left
and never returned.
I really miss her.
She died seven
years ago today.
♪
But she had a great spirit.
She never stopped believing.
(gasps)
♪
I'm so glad you
finally came home.
Now we will be
together forever.
Even though I have
left this Earth,
our souls will never part.
♪
(water rushing)
So there you have it.
That's my story.
And it's not a fable,
it happened to me right here.
Wishing Firefly.
(water gurgling)
Somehow I feel like your
story is very familiar.
Anyway, it's late,
time for me to leave.
Wait, are you really
going home already, mister?
You be good until
I see you again.
Oh, I'll be good,
I just want to hear
more stories next time.
Uh, excuse me,
there's just one thing.
There is one important
question I want to ask you.
When a man loves a woman
and he ignores that love
to follow his goals--
I guess what I'm asking is,
do you regret it?
A wise question.
I have many regrets.
Certainly, I regret
wasting most of my life
searching for something to let
me know I was good enough.
But I think my biggest
regret is that I left behind
the true love of my life.
I never got to
experience the love
she wanted to give me.
There are so many people
who live their entire lives
searching for the love
I had and threw away.
Love is priceless
and we should all recognize
its tremendous power.
♪
I thought my story might prove
of special interest to you.
So keep loving the people
you have around you.
You're lucky to have them.
♪
I'm so glad all of you
came back safe and sound.
♪
Did you catch fish?
What happened?
Sorry, but no fish.
Well, I hope you
all had a good time.
Well, we did meet
an old fisherman
and he told
a great story to us.
Well, you'll be happy
to hear that Dr. Gensai
brought enough vegetables
and noodles for a feast.
It's almost ready.
You girls get
your hands washed.
I mean, you two are
hungry, aren't you?
-Sure, let's eat!
-I'm starving!
(laughing)
♪
From now on, I will
cherish Kori's love
like the precious
flower it is.
♪
(singing in foreign language)