♪
(singing in foreign language)
(gunshot)
(gasping)
(clinking)
Sayo?
-(gunshot)
-Ah!
Say...Sayo.
♪
So, this is how it feels
to have you holding me,
here in your arms.
Mmm...mmm.
I never told you...
...how much you mean to me.
I wish I had before now.
(coughing)
Oh, no!
No, Sayo!
♪
(panting)
That's impossible, Kenshin isn't
really serious about this.
He can't fight Shogo
without his sight.
Oh, Kenshin.
Again, Kenshin?
Do you think you can
actually defeat me sightless?
Yes, Shogo, I can.
I will because that's the only
way to bring you to your senses.
For these people to live,
you must surrender.
♪
Artillery and infantry ready,
awaiting your command, sir.
Be prepared to begin
the assault upon my command.
Yes, sir!
How many times do I have to tell
you, don't attack Holy Hill.
Kenshin Himura's over
there fixing things!
What do I have to do,
rip your legs off
to get your attention
just so you'll listen?
What's she saying, Captain?
I'm saying Kenshin's
on Holy Hill right now,
talking to Shogo Amakusa.
I'm telling you there's no need
for innocent people to die!
Place this woman
under military arrest.
Oh, pretend you have a brain,
don't destroy Shimabara!
What does it take
to get through
your armor-plated
military skulls?
(grunting)
Release that young
lady immediately!
-Huh?
-Oh.
♪
It's you, Governor Elsten.
Consul Elsten, we
welcome your presence.
Governor, I come to warn you.
You must immediately
bring to a halt the assault
on the village
of Shimabara, sir.
Huh?
This act of unwarranted
violence can harm
our international relationship.
My government views this
action with great concern.
With all due respect,
Mr. Elsten, you have
no right to interfere.
This is purely an
internal matter.
Any action that we take is
strictly our own concern, sir.
But not, sir, when you set about
murdering innocent people
merely because the faith
they believe in
happens to be Christian.
For hundreds of years,
ever since the Edo era,
you have been following
this path of awful oppression.
It must stop.
But times are difficult, sir.
I don't speak for
my government alone.
America, England, and France--
the entire international
community views this persecution
of Christians with
extreme disfavor.
If you continue, there could be
the most severe consequences
to your entire nation.
Are you prepared to fight
against the entire world?
Well, sir?
Will you listen?
I know I'm just a girl,
and I'm not supposed to know
about these things, but the
whole world's watching us.
If you massacre
these Christians,
it could lead to full scale war,
and in case you haven't noticed,
we aren't that big!
If that happens,
you're responsible.
Shogo Amakusa is a dangerous
fanatic who has broken the law.
His religion is not the issue,
only the subversive acts
he's planning to commit
against the government.
And that's exactly why
Kenshin Himura is up there
right now convincing
him to surrender.
I firmly believe this
can be solved peacefully.
Mr. Himura is famous
as a Royalist
of the Meiji Restoration.
I think he can achieve
surrender without bloodshed.
Attacking these Christian
people would be a mistake, sir.
Mr. Elsten, there are many
factors at work here, sir.
Captain?
This is a military matter,
which is really not your affair.
Rebellion against the government
is punishable by death.
No.
You're crazy.
However, I will do this for you.
You seem to think this Kenshin
can perform miracles.
Very well, let him.
I will give him one hour to
arrange Shogo's surrender.
But if he fails, we attack.
Lieutenant, prepare to
move out in one hour.
One hour, sir.
And if there's the
slightest resistance,
we will crush it to death.
Good day, sir.
(sighing)
♪
If you can't get
Shogo to surrender,
then they'll all be massacred.
A blind man to save
a madman from another madman.
Oh, Kenshin.
What's going on?
Shogo has been challenged.
Isn't that Kenshin Himura?
Yes, but I heard
he lost his sight.
Maybe he wants
Lord Shogo to heal him.
No, it was Lord Shogo that
blinded him in the first place.
Some people don't know
when they're ahead.
Maybe we should take
the children away.
After that, I can't believe
he'd come back here.
You're telling me to surrender,
ordering me to.
(chuckling)
(laughing)
No one gives orders to
Shogo Amakusa, no one!
To think that I would ever stand
still for such humiliation.
My death will be proud and holy,
and all of my followers
will join me in Heaven.
No, Shogo, that's not what
you believe in your heart.
Just what do you mean?
It's strange.
Even though my eyes
can't see your face,
my blindness helps me see
more clearly into your heart.
The truth is in there.
I've seen that truth, Shogo,
since our katanas crossed
on the night of thunder cry.
Huh?
That night, your Hiten Mitsurugi
technique achieved a perfection
that was almost beyond human.
Almost.
Each sword stroke shocked me
with an indescribable power.
Your passion and your
strength were fueled
by the very essence
of Mitsurugi.
In your final stroke, its power
took the blood from my flesh,
the fire from my arms,
the sight from my eyes.
♪
That's when I saw your spirit--
the will, the need, the desire
to give others protection.
The death of another
kills a part of you.
My heart saw the truth
in your heart.
Even if the life is
taken from an enemy,
your soul weeps tears
of blood at the loss.
You try to be so cold,
your speech sounds hard,
unyielding as stone,
but sometimes you can't
frighten an enemy away.
You have no choice but to kill,
and oh, the price you pay.
You expect me to believe you
could possibly lead these people
to their deaths without knowing
full well the consequences?
Recognizing you will spend
all of eternity suffering
unspeakable grief
because of what you did,
the lives you lost?
This is Hiten Mitsurugi.
Himura, you know--
you know the pain
and the grief that I feel
every single day that I awaken.
The grief of knowing my destiny
is to take those lives
whether I want to or not.
♪
That's exactly why I must
do something, Shogo.
(panting)
♪
Oh, Kenshin.
Very well, then.
You leave me no
choice but to test
your mastery of the
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
I'm sorry.
♪
I decide when I die.
First, I will defeat you.
That will be my last miracle.
Then, on this holy day,
I will fight the murdering army,
and at a time
that I choose,
I will die and go to
Heaven with my followers.
♪
Double time, march!
Forward, quickly!
Mr. Elsten, we've
got to do something.
I'm going up the hill right now
to see if Kenshin has talked
Shogo into surrendering yet.
I'll give you a signal
from up there.
Then, do everything you
can to stop the attack.
Mmm hmm, good luck to you.
(panting)
♪
It's beginning.
The battle of two
Mitsurugi masters.
If Kenshin can
defeat Shogo here,
the Seal of Rai Ryu Sen
will be broken.
And what's even more important,
Kenshin will regain his sight.
Kori, I don't get it.
How is Kenshin
supposed to fight anyone
if he can't see his opponent?
How can he defend
himself from Shogo
if he's got that
sort of handicap?
It won't be easy.
He should be able to remember
some of Shogo's
movement patterns.
Remember that they did fight
once before and they're both
champion swordsmen
in Hiten Mitsurugi.
-And also--
-And also...?
Well, Kenshin's luck.
You know what
Kenshin always says:
"It's smarter to be lucky
than it's lucky to be smart."
But Kenshin is lucky.
He's pretty smart.
I just hope his luck holds out.
It absolutely has to.
There are too many lives
depending on the
outcome of this.
It has to!
♪
Kenshin, you're defeated!
Huh?
Ha, he stopped Shogo!
Twin dragon blocking
twin dragon!
Surrender, Shogo.
No, never!
Never--my choice, my choice!
(grunting)
I can sense that
you're bleeding,
but I didn't strike you.
That's not your concern, Himura.
(panting)
Get up, Shogo.
Kenshin Himura is every bit
as good as Lord Shogo,
even if he is blind.
How could he wound Lord Shogo
without even using his blade?
Shogo, I know you've been shot,
and now your blood
stains the ground.
Stop now.
Oh, you're a talkative one.
You're trying to distract me
from the business at hand,
which is your death!
Are you still trying to paint
yourself as God's chosen one?
Your body is
wounded and bleeding
just like your spirit
is wounded and bleeding.
The massacre of your mother
and father wounded you
because you could do
nothing to stop it.
You decided the only way to help
others was to convince them
divine power flows through you,
but all you've really done
is hurt them by playing God.
Shut up!
(groaning)
Oh, my gosh!
♪
It's agony that
you're not really God.
You suffer that you can't save
those who believe in you.
Failure, guilt that you could
not save your sister's life--
no, Shogo, you're not
allowed to have that guilt.
You wanted your sister
and all these people here
to be completely
happy now, on Earth,
but that's not in
the power of a mere man.
You can't just make people
happy by wishing it to be so.
Remember Shogo, you said
that there's happiness eternal
and unending to be
found in Heaven.
Well, there's just
one small problem.
To achieve that, all of your
followers have to be killed off.
And you're a holy man,
you don't kill anymore,
but the army does and the army's
willing to help all these people
off the Earth and up to Heaven.
And you're willing
to let them do it.
All because you can't face
the fact that you're not God.
You're just a man, Shogo.
♪
Be a man...face yourself.
(breathing weakly)
So, Shogo, you've
finally come to visit me.
It's the first time
since you took my sight.
This proves to me that you now
know that prideful actions
will gain you nothing
but more pain.
How much longer
will you dare to claim
the title of God's Chosen One?
It is a heavy burden,
so are you positive
that you can carry its weight?
It's not a problem for me.
It helps to give my life
a lot more direction.
This is my power,
to save the people,
to baptize them into the truth.
With Amakakeru Ryu no Hirameki.
Shogo, why won't
you understand?
You're bright,
you had such promise.
But your Amakakeru
Ryu no Hirameki
is based in hatred.
Your mind is clouded
with self-doubt.
One day you'll be defeated
by one who does not need
eyes to see the truth.
(panting)
♪
Kenshin Himura, the time
has come to see who is right,
whether it's you or me.
Our blades will decide.
So, prepare to die.
There is no way your
Amakakeru Ryu no Hirameki
can stand against my
Amakakeru Ryu no Hirameki.
♪
It's true!
Shogo's actually going
to go through with it.
Kenshin also.
Two masters of
Amakakeru Ryu no Hirameki.
♪
It's up to you to choose
your own path, your decision.
Kenshin, please
take care of Shogo.
He will need your help...please.
♪
Everything I am must
go into this blade.
♪
Shogo, you must be
prepared to someday
give everything
to save Shimabara.
I will!
Protect those who have
been mistreated, my son.
Forget pity--
be strong, Shogo,
strong as the steel of a blade.
I will...I will be
strong with no pity.
I'll fight bad people
and help good people.
I'll save everyone.
I will.
What have I done?
Who have I fought?
I've drawn steel
against people I love,
and deserted people who love me.
I've failed to save
those closest to me.
Don't worry, sister,
I'll always keep you safe.
I was much happier
then than I realized.
I knew nothing about hate.
When did I learn it?
When did I give up my innocence?
♪
When did I lose
my faith in others?
And when did I lose myself?
What did I forget
about humanity?
And what did I
willingly throw away?
I can never go back.
I'm lost...lost.
♪
Oh, no, he's dead, he's dead!
He was invincible!
(indistinct chatter)
Whoa!
(gasping)
♪
(gasping for air)
Finish it...go ahead.
Right now...finish it.
It's over.
I'm no good to
anyone any longer.
I can't save anyone.
I'm not God's child,
I'm not a holy man.
I'm not a healer--
just a man.
Good to no one.
Ohh.
Oh, please don't die,
please don't die, Lord Shogo.
Please, please don't leave us.
(indistinct conversation)
Don't leave us, don't die!
Lord Shogo, Lord Shogo!
You helped us,
how can we help you?
Lord Shogo, you've helped us,
protected us for so long.
If you leave us, Lord Shogo,
we can't go on without you.
We don't know what to do.
No one has ever given so much
to the village of Shimabara.
No one has ever cared for us
as much as Lord Shogo has.
Lord Shogo, please
help this old woman.
Give me strength.
How can we find a safe
and happy place to live
if Lord Shogo's
not around to help?
We need you to live to help us
build our Christian lives.
You must live!
Please don't die on us.
(indistinct chatter)
♪
(crowd crying)
Lord Shogo, please don't die.
We all need your help and
your guidance in our lives.
We need you.
We can't go on
without you, Lord Shogo.
♪
Help us!
Please promise you won't die.
Promise to stay with us.
Please, promise you'll live.
I...promise.
(crowd crying)
♪
Kenshin.
We did it, Kori.
(gasping)
You can see!
-You can see again!
-It's true.
Yes, and you're
a sight for sore eyes.
I'm so glad.
♪
I'm so glad!
(crying)
Kenshin, I knew that
you could pull it off.
Kenshin!
Hey, Kenshin!
What happened?
Did I miss anything, tell me.
A miracle happened here,
Misao, a miracle.
And Kenshin did it!
No, the people of
Shimabara did it.
Their love saved
someone who'd forgotten
what it's like to be a man,
but now, Shogo Amakusa
is finally home.
♪
(singing in foreign language)