♪
In our last episode, Sano was
forced to fight for his life
in a deadly duel with
the depraved monk, Anji.
So long!
(grunts)
♪
Go on, finish him.
(chanting)
Don't start
chanting just yet.
Huh?
I'm a quick learner
and I just learned
another one of your moves.
Hmm?
Having negate
the force of impact
by a simultaneous strike
to the opposing
side of my own body.
Thanks for the lesson.
(yells)
(groans)
No!
Good for you, Sano.
I knew he could do it.
(breathing heavily)
How'd you do it, Sano?
I watched what he did and used
his own moves against him.
I hope he's still alive.
I didn't want to kill him.
He was different once.
A man with a good heart
and noble intentions,
but he lost his way.
He was my friend
before he went insane.
Oh!
It can't be!
(groaning)
I don't believe it.
(retches)
(groaning)
That's a mortuary tablet.
Even in battle, you carry
the names of your
dead near your heart.
Why Anji?
Why?
These are...
all the names of those
who are pure of heart
but couldn't be saved.
(grunts)
For you to understand, you
must know where it all began.
Ten years ago, the year of
the anti-Buddhist movement.
That's my toy!
Give it back!
(children laughing)
Give it back, gimme!
(boy laughing)
Hey!
Masuki,
stop that!
That's Goru's toy,
now stop teasing her,
and Goru, you stop
being such a crybaby.
-You understand?
-Uh-huh.
Now go and do
your chores.
You can start by
getting the water.
Go on!
-Yes Mama!
And as for you,
Father Anji,
you spoil these kids rotten
by always being nice to them.
You have to get
angry at them sometimes
or they'll never behave.
But I'm not good
at getting mad.
I don't think I could.
You have to
try harder then.
If you're a human being,
you have to let your
anger out once in a while
or you're gonna go crazy.
I'll try, all right?
You'd better.
Please tell Tasuki to stop
throwing snow down my back.
(woman fussing)
Now, what
does Buddha know?
-The truth that's in our heart.
Look, Father Anji,
I wrote it down.
Listen children, Buddha is
always going to watch over you.
Especially at times like this
when your parents are away.
Buddha has a special
place in his heart
that he's reserved just
for little children.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Buddha is good to us and
will answer our prayers.
Then will he answer me
and make me taller?
Will spring
get here sooner?
And he can make you and
Tsubaki get married sooner too!
-Huh?
We've been praying hard
for you to take
Tsubaki as your wife.
We know you like each other,
so what are you waiting for?
Go on and ask her.
Yeah, hurry up.
Please ask her.
Be quiet, I forbid you
to talk about this.
Let's go ask Runa.
He'll make sure
they get married.
Those poor kids
don't have anyone.
They don't have any family.
They want us
to get married
because they think
that will make them
part of a family again.
Sounds good.
Oh!
I will-- I really like
the gift you gave me.
I'll treasure it forever.
See ya soon!
♪
What?
You want to tear
down the temple?
Our wise rulers
in the Meiji government
have decided to
support the nationwide
anti-Buddhist movement.
Not wanting to
offend the government,
the villagers have decided
to tear the temple down.
I don't mind leaving,
but what about
those poor children
I've been taking care of?
Their parents were all
killed in the boshin war
and they don't have
any place to go.
Ha!
Those poor children
are one of the reasons
this village is in so
much trouble right now.
Their fathers supported the
Tokugawa in the boshin war,
so the Meiji government
still looks on this village
with suspicion.
So, the other villagers
resent those kids
whose fathers have caused
this village so much trouble.
Because of what they did,
our village isn't receiving
any of the reconstruction money
that the Meiji government
is handing out.
And now that temple of yours
is just making matters worse.
You must leave at once.
Talking is a
waste of time.
Just leave it to me
and I'll get rid of
our problem in one night.
Hmm?
They're just a bunch
of dirty little orphans
and one impoverished priest
without a single parishioner.
No one's gonna care
how we treat them.
Villages that were loyal
to the Meiji government
have been given huge
amounts for renovation
but it's only
a matter of time
before the reconstruction
fund is depleted.
If we want to get any of
the government's money,
we have to act quickly.
You're right.
Oh, Father Anji?
Huh?
Will they tear down
the temple where we live?
They say that we're gonna
have to leave the village.
You said if we prayed everything
was gonna be all right.
They say we're gonna
have to leave because--
because of what
our fathers did.
(chuckling)
Your fathers were
all good men.
I know they were, because
they hated war and killing,
but regardless of
what side they fought on,
the goal they
were praying
and working
for was peace.
They did nothing for
you to be ashamed of
and were guilty of
nothing dishonorable.
So, you needn't worry.
Your mothers and fathers
wanted you to be happy,
and that is my
prayer for you as well.
Hey, there's no reason for
you guys to look so sad,
because I've got
a surprise for you.
We'll leave together
and start all over
as a family in a new
and wonderful land.
Would you like that?
(astonished gasps)
Let's go to Tokyo!
They say it's the most wonderful
city in the whole world.
I wanna go to Kyoto.
How about Hakodate?
Silly, Hakodate's in
the middle of the fighting.
We can't go there,
it's too dangerous.
Darn!
(kids talking over each other)
Merciful and
compassionate Buddha,
please watch over
these children.
Protect them with the strength
of your indomitable spirit.
They've been
through so much.
Lost everything and
suffered so much pain.
Please protect them.
Give them a future
filled with happiness.
♪
What's the matter?
Can't you sleep?
Oh, sorry about
that Tsubaki.
I mean, I hope
I didn't wake you.
♪
No, please
don't worry.
I'm strong, I swear I can
help you and I'll work hard.
I have to watch
over the others.
I'm the oldest.
You have a lot of other
things to worry about,
so I'll watch them.
I know you will.
Listen, Buddha will
get us through anything
as long as we believe
in him and work together.
Now, please Tsubaki,
go back to sleep
and try to get
some rest all right?
♪
Buddha, divine
light, help us.
Protect us from
the forces of evil
and bring us
all inner peace.
Please.
I left the temple for
my cleansing ritual
and stayed longer than usual.
I saw the flames.
I realized that the villagers
had an agenda of their own.
They had never
intended to allow me
or my flock to leave
the temple alive.
♪
No!
(shuddering)
Tsubaki!
Goru, Tsuki!
Where are you?
Mikon, Yohi,
can you hear me?
Where are you?
(groans)
Stupid!
That's the last of them.
Hmm, they should have left
when they had the chance.
Now, the Meiji government will
give us all the help we need.
♪
Merciful Buddha,
I know you have a plan
for all living things,
that you have a reason for
everything that happens
in this world,
but please,
please, don't allow
evil to triumph.
I beg you,
merciful Buddha,
to defend the
innocent children
who depend on you
to protect them.
♪
(screaming)
Why?
♪
Why, Buddha, why did
this have to happen?
♪
But Buddha
didn't answer me,
and I realized he
hadn't forsaken me.
Because Buddha
wasn't responsible
for what had happened.
It was men.
Men corrupted by greed
and the promise of
power who were to blame,
and I vowed to
make them pay
for what they had done.
♪
(screaming)
(whimpering)
Please, I beg you,
have mercy.
Please!
♪
(screaming)
(speaking foreign language)
♪
Do you understand?
Everything
that I believed in,
everyone
I loved was gone.
My entire life
had been a lie.
Prayer doesn't
lead to salvation.
It merely focuses
one's ability
to cleanse the world
by creating a new one!
The only way to
create a new world
is to destroy the old one.
♪
Until the day
those children
have completed the
cycle of reincarnation,
until their souls are
reborn into this world,
I'll see to it
that they return
to a better world
than the one they left.
Stop this!
Stay out of it,
Kenshin.
♪
(screaming)
He's gone crazy.
(yelling)
♪
(yells)
You wanna die?
Then die!
♪
(grunting)
Just like I was.
♪
(yells)
I was full of
hate like you!
♪
You know nothing.
I lost everyone.
Everyone I ever loved.
After that, hate was
the only thing I had left.
♪
(grunting)
If I hadn't met Kenshin,
that hatred would
have destroyed me.
♪
And now you're just
like I used to be.
Hatred and revenge are the only
things you really care about.
Do you wanna talk
or do you wanna fight?
(panting)
♪
I don't understand.
They're hitting
each other with blows
that have enough force
to kill an entire army,
yet they're
still standing.
Either one of them could
fall just about any time now.
The only thing sustaining
the two of them now
is their conviction
that they have to win.
(yelling)
These two have
the hearts of lions,
and even though
they're both exhausted,
as long as they use the
extreme fist technique,
they're pretty much equal.
I suspect otherwise.
Consider this,
Anji is a priest and
priests don't use swords,
but he's also a member
of the Juppongatana
and though he hasn't used it
yet, carries a sword himself.
I can't help
wondering why.
(gasps)
♪
(screams)
(breathing heavily)
(groans)
What was that?
Strike from afar.
Anji doesn't use
the sword directly,
but he's still able to use
the extreme fist technique
by transferring the
energy force of the blow
through the ground.
Meaning Anji will win.
As long as he
keeps his distance,
Sagara doesn't have
any way of striking back.
♪
(yells)
Watch out, Sano!
It's time, Anji.
Time to stop hating.
Time to stop hurting.
Let go of what was
and face the now.
Purge the rage
from your heart
or it will
destroy your soul.
Rage is my friend.
It is the only
emotion I trust
because all the
others are temporary.
My rage is always there.
To inspire me, to show me
the true path to salvation,
and you shall feel
it as I do, Sano.
You shall feel it now.
You still don't
get it, you fool.
You're the one you really
blame for what happened,
because you weren't able to
protect the ones you loved.
You'll never be able
to forgive anyone
until you forgive yourself.
♪
I think I can walk
now, Brother Anji.
You don't have
to carry me anymore.
I don't mind.
Does your leg still hurt?
It's a lot better now.
I just sprained it a little.
You just relax and
don't move that leg
anymore than you have to.
Know what I wish?
I wish that somehow we
could stop time right now.
♪
That nothing
would ever change.
That we could stay
as happy as we are
at this very moment
forever and ever.
Wouldn't that
be wonderful?
♪
Even after
I've grown old,
I am never
going to leave you.
I will be
with you always.
Forever, till
the end of time.
♪
How could anyone really
care for me so deeply?
♪
Care for a man responsible
for so many deaths.
A man who took the
lives of so many people.
(sobbing)
♪
Hey, Father Anji!
Father Anji.
Father?
Remember what
you taught us?
That Buddha's
mercy is infinite
and we have
to have faith
that he'll forgive
whatever we have done.
That's what
you taught us.
We'll always be there.
Part of you within
your heart and soul.
We will always be here.
-Always.
(ghosts repeating
"Forever and always")
♪
Anji, get up!
What are you
waiting for?
He's helpless, you fool!
Kill him and
get it over with.
♪
Your eyes look
different now, Anji.
You don't have the
eyes of a killer anymore.
You have another chance
to be the kind
priest you used to be
and continue your work
of offering salvation.
No, I've tried kindness.
It doesn't work.
There was a time when I
felt the same as you, Anji.
Not now.
Those kids,
the ones whose names
are inscribed on
that mortuary tablet,
they found salvation
in your kindness
until the very end
of their lives.
For the sake of those kids,
you can't give up now.
♪
I was wrong.
So very, very wrong.
♪
Kenshin,
did I win?
Yeah, no doubt
about that, Sano.
That's good, but I
got to hand it to him.
He sure put
up a good fight.
I'm totally wiped out.
Couldn't lift a finger.
Can you guys just go
on ahead without me?
Promise
I'll catch up.
Just need to
rest a while.
Hmm!
So, the first
duel is over.
Come now, Miss Kamagata,
we haven't got all day.
Who's next?
Wait!
You can't stay here.
You've got to
get back to Aoiya.
That's where the Juppongatana
is headed right now.
I'm one of only four
who are still here.
Seijuro, Usui,
Hoji and me.
The rest are on the way to
massacre everyone in Aoiya.
Shishio!
No!
Not Shishio, see it wasn't
his idea, it was Hoji's.
Shishio has always been
an honorable man.
He wouldn't be part of
a massacre, trust me.
As much as I'd like
to argue that point,
I don't have the time.
Let's get on
with the next duel.
I'm glad you know
that you have no choice.
If you tried to get back
to Aoiya through the maze,
you'd get lost
and probably die.
We never intended to leave.
We'll fight as
we said we would
and hope that we can
perform as courageously
and as honorably as Sano has.
Do you happen to have
any medicine with you?
Yes, I have
some right here.
Good, leave it with me.
I'll do everything
I can for him.
♪
I'd appreciate that.
Let's get this over with.
We've got to get back
there as soon as we can.
People of Aoiya
don't have a chance
against the Juppongatana.
♪
Shishio has sent his
whole army against us.
We are surrounded
and there's no way out.
♪
Come back quickly, Kenshin,
there isn't much time.
♪
This is where the second
duel will be fought.
I assure you that
if you enter this room,
you won't come out alive.
We've heard enough,
let's do it.
Whoa!
We're here
and we're ready.
Where's the guy
we're supposed to fight?
Usui!
Where are you?
♪
Here.
Glad you could come.
Usui!
Shut up, slut.
When I'm through
here Shishio will be next.
And then you'll be lucky
if I let you lick my feet.
(gasps)
I'd say
you're an optimist.
Really?
I'd say
I'm a realist.
Just the two of you?
I'll use you for practice
and then kill Shishio.
I'm ready, are you?
I wonder which one of you
wants to die first.
♪