♪
(singing in foreign language)
(water rushing)
♪
(grunting)
So, that's the best you've got?
♪
Hey, kid.
You still alive?
Hey kid, what's your problem?
-Snap out of it.
-Can't you see he's in shock?
Ah, he's a good as dead.
I better do him a favor
and just take him out.
Huh?
(groaning)
Who the hell are you?
It doesn't really matter.
You'll be dead soon.
Did you, did you see what he--
Run!
♪
It's all over now.
You're safe, and no one
is going to hurt you.
There was no choice.
I had to kill them or
they might have killed you.
♪
The dead can never
come back to life.
The only things left
for us are memories.
You're lucky that you
survived this slaughter.
Were some of these people part
of your family or something?
Huh?
You better go to
the nearest village
and explain what happened.
I'm sure someone
will take ya in.
♪
I was just thinking about
the first time we met.
Wow, that was a
lot of years ago.
So, when are you
planning to get up?
(groaning)
It looks like you're gonna
take a little longer to get up,
but that doesn't
bother me a bit.
Ah, the old days.
I remember the first
time you wet the bed.
You were eight and half.
You were so hungry, you ate
a bunch of laughing mushrooms,
and you were laughing so hard
that you peed
everywhere you went,
and all over everything.
You almost died, but since you
lived it's a very funny memory.
What about your past, Master?
You're only the tenth
person to achieve the title
of master in Hiten
Mitsurugi style.
Your skill is unparalleled,
but your personality
is a dark enigma no
one can decipher.
-Really?
-You're rude.
-You're right.
-Impatient.
I see.
And on top of being
unsociable, you remember
any mistakes your rivals
might have made in the past.
You know me, but tell me,
how would you have acted
if your young foolish pupil
left you on bad terms
without thanking you
after you spent
years teaching him?
Should I have baked a cake?
-Huh?
-Now, let's get serious.
If you can't defeat
me with your next blow,
then I'm never going
to teach you the secret.
♪
I can't try any cute
little tricks on him.
This is my last chance to get
him to teach me the secret.
I better pull out all the stops,
and put everything I've got
into this next attack.
I think my best move
is to go vertical,
and go after him like
my life depends on it.
Well, here goes nothing.
♪
(yelling)
Don't look, Kenshin, don't look.
(crying)
(groaning)
♪
I beg of you, don't kill him,
he's just a child, no!
(screaming)
Please let him live.
Let him live.
Hey, Kenshin.
You've been out
long enough, wake up.
♪
You were concentrating
so hard on your technique,
you didn't pay attention
to your landing.
So you knocked yourself out,
but there is some good news.
♪
Your stairway from heaven
charge was so strong
you actually got me on the arm.
Huh?
You're anticipating.
You're three moves ahead.
All those mind games
are keeping you
from what you do best,
but you have proven to me that
I should teach you the secret.
So, now we shall begin.
First, we must review the
types of attack used in Kendo.
Karatake.
Kesagiri.
Sakagesa.
Hidarinagi.
Miginagi.
Hidarikiriage.
Migikiriage.
Sakakaze.
Tsuki.
No matter what the
technique or style is
there are only nine
slash attacks,
and all defensive
counter-attacks
are also based on these nine
Kendo attack variations.
-However...
-Huh?
(yelling)
By using the Hiten
Mitsurugi sword style
you can deliver all nine thrusts
with such god-like speed
that no defense strategy
can withstand your attack.
It's virtually
impossible to counteract.
My special variation is the
nine-head dragon thrust.
Unbelievable.
I couldn't defend against
it or even avoid it.
I didn't even move.
That's some secret.
Kenshin, stop standing
there like a Bonsai tree,
and give the move a try.
But I don't even
know where to start!
I thought I taught you
to have more confidence.
But I barely saw it!
You know that in order
to master anything,
you must make an effort.
That's how I came up with
this, by taking a skill,
honing on it, then building on
it to create something new.
Isn't that how you
improved your skills?
Whoa!
Frankly, I'm
surprised I survived.
Well, to be honest with
you, you only survived
because I took it
very easy on you.
(laughs)
This is not the time for
you to be self-critical.
Now, give it a try.
♪
Even though I didn't move,
I did see what he was doing.
Now, I have to remember it
and break it down into steps.
(yelling)
There, I can see them.
All nine slashing attacks
being manifested at once.
Get ready.
Because my mind's
eye can see it,
now the movements make
sense to my muscles.
♪
(yelling)
I gotta start thinking about
my landing after my attack.
At least I got through
it in pretty good shape,
considering it was
the first time.
Wow, I haven't moved
that fast in a long time.
Did it look to you
like I did that right?
Please, Master, talk to me.
Your nine-dragon attack
was almost perfect,
but even using the same
technique, the effect will have
different results depending
on who's delivering it.
When you do a rough attack,
arm strength is important,
and when you're charging
someone, having some weight
can be really helpful.
Two factors that make your
attack inferior to mine.
In other words, your nine-dragon
attack doesn't match up well
to mine, because you need
to be heavier and stronger
to do it better than me.
I don't have time to
gain strength or weight
so I guess this attack
won't work for me.
I hope he can think of
another way to help him
prove my chances
against Shishio.
Relax.
I have another power
technique that can defeat
the nine-dragon attack,
but if I teach it to you,
you must swear to me to
keep it an absolute secret.
This technique I developed
is called Hirameki,
but can you keep it
a secret forever?
Of course.
You should feel very flattered
because I've never shared
this form with anybody else.
I'm ready!
This secret you wish
to know can be found
within the nine-dragon attack.
Think about how
to stop its speed,
and you'll find the secret.
So, this other secret
is a riddle I must solve.
Think!
-Huh?
-Good luck.
By the way, here's an excellent
hint that might just help you.
Listen, the nine-dragon
thrust is my own technique,
but I only showed
you half of it.
Huh?
That's just great.
Discovering this secret
was one of the greatest
breakthroughs I've ever made.
You see, by teaching the
nine-dragon attack style,
I found a way to beat it,
and I'm not just gonna
tell you the secret.
You must think it
through yourself.
If you can beat me with
your nine-dragon attack
without more weight
or strength than me,
than in that process you will
find the secret that you seek.
Think about the kendo components
that make up this attack.
What characteristics
change when you speed up
each of the nine
slashing movements?
You'll find the answer.
So, I'll learn the
answer through experience.
(thunder rumbling)
♪
Since this attack is too
quick to avoid or defend,
the only thing that
can logically work
is to thrust in before
the attack begins.
That is correct.
Batu technique can beat
the god-like speed.
Now you have pinpointed the
first part which is Hirameki,
but that can only
work if he can pull
his reversed-edge sword
from his sheath quickly,
and with that kind of
sword it won't be easy.
♪
It's time.
Huh?
I see from your stance
that you have given up.
Have you lost your nerve,
or are you just thinking?
♪
You look confused.
I'm not afraid to try...
or die.
♪
Well?
I think you wanna
keep me confused,
because you don't want
me to be better than you.
♪
(rain pouring)
Master!
Is it that you expect
me to coddle you
because you're unsure
of how good you are?
You'll never master the secret
until you know yourself.
(rain pouring)
(sighing)
I have to choose which
Kenshin I want to be.
♪
I'm going to give you overnight
to think about what I just said.
Search inside your heart
and find what's missing,
and if you can't figure it
out, not only can you not
learn the secret,
but more importantly--
I know, if I can't help myself
I won't be able to help
anyone else either.
♪
What is it that keeps me
from believing in myself?
Tell me, did a little
boy show up here today?
-Kind of skinny and quiet.
-Nope.
You know, I heard
about that massacre,
but I haven't seen a soul.
Just thought I'd check.
I guess he must have
died of a broken heart.
Thanks anyway.
♪
Maybe the kid got so
depressed he killed himself.
Probably figured he had
nothing left to live for.
I tried to help him.
I guess he was just too
far gone emotionally.
Still, I feel sorry for him.
Maybe I should've
taken him in myself.
Nah, probably wouldn't
have worked out either.
I try to help
people with my sword,
but it seems like
it's almost a curse.
Well, I'll try to find his
body and at least bury him.
Huh?
♪
Did you spend all night
burying your parents?
No, my parents died a year ago.
I was burying my friends
that tried to protect me,
and I also buried the two
thieves you saved me from.
What are those three
stones there for?
I mean, what do they signify?
My dearest friends, all three
of them sacrificed their lives
so I could live.
Satoko, Mitsumi, and Kasumi.
When my parents were
killed they took me in.
They raised me as their
own, but there was no money
so we were traveling to another
town when we were ambushed.
I tried to fight the thieves
but they wouldn't let me.
I dragged the best stones
I could find to here
to mark their graves.
I wish I could've found
some flowers for them.
♪
I will honor them by sharing
my best sake with them.
It's the least I can do.
They've left us
for a better place.
♪
-So boy, what's your name?
-Shinta.
That name's too gentle for
a boy with such a rough life.
I will train you to survive
so you must have
a swordsman's name.
-From now on you are Kenshin.
-Huh?
Himura, you are Kenshin Himura
and you will be a sword fighter.
♪
That day was almost
19 years ago.
(rain pouring)
And tomorrow will be
our final goodbye.
Oh, scary!
Tell us another
ghost story, Grandpa!
No, that's enough
stories for now.
Then tell us when we're
going to see Kenshin again.
Yes, when, Grandpa?
Well, he's out there somewhere.
Hopefully he'll come back
some time this week.
What?
But you said that last week!
I hope Kenshin
will come back soon.
Yes, very soon.
♪
Yoshi, isn't it about time
to come out of the rain?
-Okay!
-You're gonna catch a cold!
I've got an umbrella!
I can't believe
it's still raining.
With any luck, Himura will learn
the secret technique from Hiko
and come home soon.
-But he--
-What?
Kenshin has a habit of
handling problems by himself
instead of teaming
up with someone.
That makes me worry about him.
I know it's important to
know a higher technique
when he's fighting Shishio's
gang, but he might do better
to organize a group
to help him instead.
Besides, the toughest battle
he's fighting is within himself
between Battousai and Kenshin.
What am I saying?
Here I am pouring
out my heart to you,
and you probably don't
even want to hear this.
No, I do share your concerns,
but I don't feel there's
a need to worry about him.
Kenshin's taken care
of himself up until now,
but I do wish that Himura
would come back here.
Okina would probably
feel a lot better.
He likes Kenshin, but Kaoru,
if you need someone to talk to,
I want you to know
that I'm here for you.
Thanks, Misao.
I'm gonna go feed some
hot soup to Okina.
Um...
(shivering)
(sneezing)
♪
I can't believe you're here.
I imagine you must've
had one hell of a trip.
Just let me in, chief.
There were some delays.
Now show me the swordsman
from Shishio's group
that you arrested.
I believe his name is Cho.
Sure, I got him stuck
in a cell in the back.
Over here.
I said over here.
It's you.
Huh, yeah, it's me all right.
Sanosuke Sagara
has arrived in Edo.
♪
So, tell me, Kenshin.
Have you found out what it
is that's missing for you?
No, sir.
I must admit, I'm
surprised you had the guts
to come here and
tell me to my face.
You're wise to know your limits,
and it's better you
discovered that your skills
are mediocre here
than finding that out
in the middle of a sword
battle with Shishio.
You can't even win
the battle inside you.
You'll live the rest
of your life in pain
unless you get past this block.
So, let's get to it.
Come on, Kenshin.
You won't be able
to live with yourself
if you don't at least try.
♪
I created your skills,
and I can take you out.
It's your move, Kenshin.
Come on.
♪
Am I afraid of Seijuro Hiko,
or do I fear that battling
him would result in death?
It can't be that,
because I've faced death
fearlessly many times.
I'm not that attached to life.
At the end of the Tokugawa era
I was actually hoping to die,
and my feelings haven't
changed much since then.
Wait!
Now I understand!
I'm more afraid of killing
my master than dying myself.
Come on, don't be afraid!
(yelling)
♪
I was the only boy, so even
though I was scared to die
I felt like I had
to defend my friends,
and I knew these men were better
than me, and I was terrified.
Shinta, listen to me.
You are young, so you must
survive, you must live.
No matter what happens,
you deserve to live.
You're young and
haven't had the chance
to be able to
choose your destiny.
Long after we are gone you
will earn the right to decide
how you want to live
your life, Shinta.
Choose to live!
I must live, for all of them.
(shouting)
♪
Yes, you must live.
You have killed so many that
you see your life as having
little value,
but you must live
to fight against evil.
As you struggle against
your inner demons,
you have tried to protect
the ones you love,
and you've fought for
those who are too weak
to defend themselves.
Continue to battle
the slasher inside you,
yet use his ruthlessness when
nothing else can help you.
Then you can use Hirameki
in the way you want,
and not lose yourself to
the slasher within you.
And don't worry about me.
My fate is deserved.
This is what becomes of a master
who taught through fear
instead of kindness.
♪
And this incident has
in no way violated
your non-killing promise.
Kenshin, you were always
my favorite pupil,
and I guess I kept you
unsure so you would always
need me in your life.
Now go and destroy Shishio.
(groaning)
No!
♪
No.
Sensei!
♪
(singing in foreign language)