♪
(singing in Japanese)
No!
Leave her alone!
Don't touch her, you brute!
(yelling)
(grunting)
♪
Daigoro!
(grunting)
♪
No!
Please wake up!
Daigoro, please, please wake up!
Don't you dare die!
You can't give up!
I don't believe it.
Neither do I.
(sobbing)
♪
You were warned not to
tamper with my affairs,
now you will all surely die.
-You will die!
-Stop!
I'll handle it, we don't
need any more bloodshed.
All right.
♪
What are you waiting
for, kill him!
(grunting)
(growling)
It's no wonder Katsu relies
on you to do his dirty work.
I feel I betrayed his trust,
he didn't want me to help him.
(sobbing)
Nobody can be allowed to
interfere the Beni Aoi.
I guess I'll have to
stop you by myself.
My men will take
care of the others.
Yes, sir.
♪
(grunting)
All right, whoever
wants a piece of me next,
I am ready for them!
Fine, then come get me.
I'm happy to avenge
the kidnapping of Itsuko,
and for what you just did.
For Daigoro!
Each strike will
be for Daigoro!
(screaming)
I know you've kidnapped
Katsu's daughter to force
him into coming here so
you can kill him, but why?
The first step, the Beni Aoi
plan can be implemented
once he's been eliminated.
What did he that made
you hate him so much?
Because of him,
the shogun decided
to surrender disgracefully
without even putting up a fight.
We samurai were not allowed
to battle, we were kicked out,
and Master Yoshinobu was
placed under house arrest
by the Meiji government.
Katsu's cowardly advice
led to his abdication.
You are wrong, Master Yoshinobu
decided that for himself.
There was a very good
reason he chose to do that,
and you should know
it as well as anyone.
To prevent further bloodshed?
That's just a lie!
The truth is that
Katsu sold him out,
and the snake has
been living comfortably
under government protection.
He paid off the Meiji police
with the Tokugawa fortune!
(growling)
♪
You're sure about
this information?
Absolutely.
You're saying
surrendering Edo Castle
was not Master Yoshinobu's idea?
Just take a look at the facts.
Kaishu Katsu gave up the
castle without a fight,
and thereby allowed
the Meiji forces
to defeat the
Tokugawa government.
Master Yoshinobu was
placed under house arrest.
He turns the Tokugawa fortune
over to Katsu for safekeeping.
This leaves Katsu
free to spend the money,
while Yoshinobu
rots in captivity.
(growling)
For ten long years,
we samurai have borne
the humiliation of that
defeat and forced into poverty.
We'll have our vengeance,
I will kill him!
Stop and think for a moment.
It doesn't do you any good
to kill Katsu right now.
First, you need to get
proof of his treason.
Otherwise, people will
think you've killed him
for your own selfish revenge,
and that isn't going
to get your people
back into the main
stream of society.
Besides, you don't
even possess a weapon,
but I have an idea
that will help you
even the score with Katsu,
and profit you politically.
In the meantime, I hate to
see a warrior without a sword.
You'll be stronger
with this at your side.
♪
I want to hear your plan.
I will gladly tell you
if you do as I ask.
♪
Exactly who are you?
(grunting)
I am a warrior, I'll
never be humiliated again!
♪
(shouting)
Please wake up.
How is he?
Did Daigoro survive?
♪
Look where he was stabbed,
Shibata was aiming
for his heart.
With a wound like that,
he never had a
chance to survive.
(grunting)
Mr. Katsu is not
the kind of person
that you've been
led to believe he is.
♪
You don't know what
we've been going through
since the Tokugawa era ended.
What makes you such
an expert on the subject?
♪
Don't assume you're
the only person
who's had a hard time
with all of this.
Right, we've all had
to make sacrifices.
♪
You've defeated
my best fighters!
♪
You will pay dearly
for this humiliation.
♪
Daigoro.
(gasps)
Itsuko, is that you?
My God, you're alive!
Oh, wow!
What happened to me?
Remember?
You were stabbed
during the fighting!
Seriously?
Ugh...
Amazing!
This is the book your
father wanted me to read!
Good book.
You can say that again,
it just saved his life.
(laughing)
Boy, you're lucky he
gave you a thick one.
Yeah, really!
What?
Oh, I get it...
(sighing)
You'll be fine, that'll
be your mark of bravery.
You had us all pretty
scared for a while.
Come on, you just
gotta stand up!
What's the matter, Itsuko?
I was so worried about you.
About me?
I'm sorry.
No, I thank you
for rescuing me.
Yeah.
♪
See here?
I wondered where that went!
All right, men, secure the area.
Where did they come from?
♪
Kenshin Himura,
is that you?
Yes sir, what are
you doing here, chief?
I was gonna ask you
the very same thing.
We were informed that
something was going on here.
But you couldn't
have been advised that
we were going to rescue Itsuko
because we planned it in secret.
You only knew that
someone was kidnapped?
That's absolutely right.
We knew a young woman
was being held here,
an anonymous letter
containing that information
was delivered to headquarters.
Actually, there
were two letters.
That's weird.
(chuckling)
Katsu decided to send the
police rather than come himself,
I'm not surprised.
His money is more
important than his daughter.
I knew he'd be
that kind of man!
♪
Let me tell you something!
Sensei's not that kind of man!
He is one of the
bravest people I know!
He survived an era when a lot
of people lost everything.
Because of that,
he feels responsible
for guiding the lives
of future generations.
(growling)
Come on, let's go.
♪
I guess we'd better let the
police handle the rest of it.
But do you think that's
going to be all right?
I mean, the police
aren't exactly friends.
Aren't they keeping
an eye on Sensei?
Don't worry, the old man
can handle that situation.
What is it, what's the matter?
I thought everything
is all right now,
why are you so troubled?
The police received
two letters anonymously.
That does seem strange,
I wonder who in the world
could have sent them.
Since your father's not here,
it's possible that he sent one.
But who would have
sent the other one?
(gasping)
What's wrong?
Of course!
♪
I thought I'd find you here.
What?
♪
Sensei.
What you're looking for,
my boy, is not here.
You're a clever youngster,
you've watched and
studied me very well.
You knew I'd never tell
where the money is,
despite the fact that my
daughter is being held hostage
to force me
into giving it up.
So you figured
the way around me
was to find the map marking the
location to the hidden funds.
You were sure that
map was in this house,
because at point
you'd seen me with it.
♪
You decided that while I
was away, rescuing Itsuko,
you'd look for the map.
It never entered your mind
that I might be wise to you.
For a smart guy,
that was a big mistake.
You see, I'm a big admirer
of your spirit and talent.
And I was even thinking
that you had the skills
to run this confused government.
But after this evening,
I'm no longer certain.
If I want to streamline
this government,
I need to put that
power in my hands!
And to do that, I'll need
an awful lot of money!
No doubt some
politician told you that.
The plans he has for my
future will be announced soon,
and if I'm in possession of
the Tokugawa money at that time,
my political prospects
will be unlimited.
There will be no stopping me.
For then I will be able to
go all the way to the top,
Sensei Kaishu!
Perhaps.
Politics is a strange
business with no guarantees.
I want the money!
I know that, but I'm sorry,
you just can't have it, Tatsuma.
That's no surprise,
I don't know why I
bothered to tell you
about how it could
benefit my career anyway.
What are you going
to do, Tatsuma?
♪
I'm going to do whatever
it takes to get that money,
you are leaving
me no choice here!
You're still the pupil,
I'm the teacher, don't forget.
Come on, show me
what you can do.
Don't do anything foolish
old man, give me the map,
and I'm out of here!
You'll have to kill me first.
That's the only way the map
will be leaving this house!
♪
Huh?
Mr. Katsu, please listen
to me, don't do this.
Do not pull your sword.
But I have to.
You again?
Itsuko's been
rescued, she's here!
What?
I'm all right.
Itsuko!
No need to make things
more complicated, Tatsuma.
Drop your weapon.
Don't be a fool.
♪
You all refuse to understand.
Possessing the money
is essential for me,
to realize all my goals!
You are wrong!
Don't do this!
♪
Tatsuma, your thinking
has become very clouded.
You should have known Mr. Katsu
was waiting for you here.
It would have saved you
that letter to the police.
Were you hoping they'd
arrest him for killing Shibata
if Shibata failed to kill him?
Was that the plot?
Shut up now!
(shouting)
♪
(grunting)
Tatsuma's giving
him a hard time.
Kenshin.
♪
I'd say this fight's over.
Hold it.
Just stay put.
Nobody gets the best
of me like this.
♪
Stop all this!
Please listen to me,
put the gun down!
This is all wrong, Tatsuma!
Daigoro, move out of the way!
I'm not going to go!
Right now!
No, I will not!
(gunshots)
♪
Oh, please, Tatsuma, I'm
begging you, don't act this way.
I can't bear to see
you filled with hatred.
Just look at yourself!
You were my role model,
I always looked up to you!
Now I don't even recognize you.
I know you understand
more than anyone else
what Sensei has taught us,
and you had such high ambitions
far greater than the rest of us.
I used to admire that.
But I'm scared that
your career ambitions
have become more powerful than
the principles you hold inside.
♪
Please don't give
up your integrity.
That's the one thing
that money can't buy
because it's priceless.
Sensei and Itsuko,
they are your family.
They love you so much.
You're right, Daigoro.
♪
I understand you had a
long talk with Tatsuma.
Yes, he said he
wanted to make up
for what he's
done and start over.
I have to believe that Tatsuma
must have always felt somewhere
deep in his heart that all his
plotting and scheming was wrong.
He hid it, even from himself,
always living in fear that you
or your father would find out.
So that's why he
organized the Beni Aoi
and made up a complicated
plot to obtain the map,
so he wouldn't be
suspected of anything?
His life had become
cloaked in mystery.
Daigoro got him
to see the light.
It looks like
he and Yoshi
are taking up studying
mysteries full time now.
This one's exciting,
I think the butler did it.
Mine's about the moon and stars
and all the mysteries
there are in the heavens.
(giggling)
That subject
suits Daigoro well.
My father says he has
a tremendous desire about
traveling to the moon in some
kind of flying ship one day.
He might just
surprise us and do it.
Hey Kenshin, come and
take a look at this!
It's kind of interesting!
Yeah?
Let me see.
You know, we never did find
out where the map was hidden.
I wonder what
happened to it.
I don't know.
Hey, don't look at me.
Odd place for a book.
Huh?
Tucked in your shirt.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
And now it's so covered
with blood, it's hard to read.
But I'll never throw
this book away, ever.
Sensei gave it to me, and
now that it's saved my life,
it's even more important.
It certainly is
an incredible book.
Can I see it for a minute?
Absolutely.
♪
Hm?
Daigoro.
Mr. Katsu has entrusted
you with his principles.
Take very good care of this
precious book, it's a treasure.
Okay.
(door creaking open)
Get up, Shibata,
you're free to go.
What?
The mastermind surrendered.
What he said was the
kidnapping was his idea,
and that you and the Beni Aoi
didn't know what you
were getting into.
Mr. Katsu has decided
not to press charges
and is requesting your release.
I'm sorry, Shibata.
Huh?
♪
(clearing throat)
I apologize.
It was my fault.
Tatsuma was my responsibility.
I should have watched
him even more closely.
♪
But...
I will not apologize
for evacuating Edo Castle
without a fight.
At the time, I thought
it was the wisest choice,
and I stand behind my decision.
I know you vehemently disagree
with that, but perhaps one day,
you will think differently.
I doubt it.
I hope that changes, I need
some good men to help me.
There's a lot I must do
before I leave this Earth.
We all have responsibilities,
even if we're not members
of the party in power.
♪
If you feel like it,
come visit me one day.
I'll be waiting for you.
♪
Let's go home
now, Daigoro,
you know how
my father worries.
He'll be upset if we're late.
Okay, let's go.
Thanks so much
for everything.
Give our regards
to Mr. Katsu.
I will, hey,
Itsuko, wait for me!
(yelling)
Oh, that hurt!
♪
(singing in Japanese)