♪
(singing in foreign language)
Touma, your last attempt
to deal with Heihachirou
and his friends
was a total failure.
You need to redeem yourself.
Any further mistakes will
result in severe punishment.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, sir.
These men can identify you.
You'll have to move quickly
so you don't endanger
our present or
future operations.
We've been making plans
for a couple of days.
Our spies say Heihachirou
has become a coward.
He won't even pick up
a sword to fight.
The other two should be easy.
One of them's nothing
more than a street punk.
And what about the other one?
The other one is a mystery man,
a swordsman.
He calls himself a wanderer.
We've had one encounter already.
♪
(grunting)
He seemed to be quite skilled.
Is he going to be a problem?
Nothing to worry about.
When the time comes,
I'll take care of him myself.
I'm looking forward to it.
We're entering the crucial
stage of our plans.
To assure success, we have
to move with lightning speed.
Keep your men in a state
of readiness at all times.
Yes, sir.
Once we take over
the government, Touma,
you'll have an important
position as head of security.
I'm honored by your trust.
♪
(laughing)
Sorry, Sano, my fault.
No need to apologize.
I don't have anything
better to do at the moment,
and now that I kinda see
what the job involves,
I kinda like being
a teacher's assistant.
That's not what I mean.
Now that the Jinpu Tai
know who you and Kenshin are,
I think they may try
to take you out.
No way, I'm like
a cat with nine lives.
Don't worry, I can
take care of myself,
and you know how good
Kenshin is with a sword.
There's nobody around
who can touch him.
Hey, is there some
kind of problem?
It's difficult, it's something
you don't want to hear.
When they fought,
I was able to evaluate
the skills of both men,
and the fact is
Touma is much better
than Kenshin.
That is absolutely ridiculous.
Kenshin is the best
swordsman around.
He's invincible,
aren't you mistaken?
No, and I'd be willing to
bet you Kenshin knows it, too.
-You're it!
-Uh-oh!
I've seen it all,
it's just not possible.
No one's better than Kenshin.
(birds chirping)
(grunting)
Who in the world would
ever have imagined it?
A school teacher who
used to be a swordsman
in part of the Kyoto Patrol?
The story gets
even more amazing.
He and Kenshin actually
fought one another years ago
when the Patrol was trying
to arrest Battousai.
I'm telling you, Doctor,
it's a small world.
It seems like it's
getting smaller every day.
A secret sword move
I just learned.
Shiden No Tachi!
Yoshi, that was a good one!
You're gonna be the
best fighter ever!
Gee, ya mean it?
Shiden No Tachi.
(grunting)
♪
(blasts)
Huh?
I'm sure he had his reasons,
but I think it's a real waste
for a guy with skills
like Heihachirou
to retire and give up
his sword forever.
But if he was going to
give up being a swordsman,
what better
occupation than teacher
so he could help kids
achieve their dreams?
I want to go to school
so I can be just as smart
as Kaoru someday!
I want to be as smart as Yumi!
You're both as smart
as a whip already.
Good for you,
that's the spirit.
Huh?
Hi, everybody.
Is Kenshin around here?
Uh, I believe I saw him
outside doing laundry.
You positive?
He was there a minute ago.
Sano.
What's the big deal,
he could've gone for a walk.
Is something wrong?
Uh, no, I'm sure
he's perfectly fine!
Really, everyone, there's
nothing to worry about!
You make a lousy liar.
What's happening, huh?
(bird chirping)
You're here, you might
as well come on out.
It's nothing personal, Himura.
You just got in the way.
And now you have to die!
(grunting)
I should've realized when I saw
the cross scar on your cheek.
You really are
Battousai the Slasher.
So why aren't you
making your move?
Because I didn't come
out here to fight,
I came here to ask you
a simple question.
What motivates you to
embrace a life of murder?
Is it the money or
are you a mad dog?
I'm no different than
you were, Battousai.
I expect to change the world
with a slash of my sword.
I'm afraid you've got it wrong.
I didn't expect to
change the world,
I simply committed murder,
and none of those killings
caused the restoration
to take place,
so why do you think
your assassinations
will be more effective?
Listen, the sword
is still the best tool
for getting rid of the corrupt
leaders who govern this country.
Maybe you didn't have any effect
because you operated alone,
without an organization to
provide support and direction.
But we have a plan,
and my sword is my
ticket to advancement.
Our leader has promised me
a position in the new order.
Yes, that brings up
an obvious question.
Who's the man
behind these killings?
Forget it, you'll never know.
(grunting)
Time to die!
♪
You realized you were
no match for me before,
and now you're
afraid for your life.
Well, you won't escape
your fate this time.
It's too late.
I wouldn't try
a Shiden No Tachi technique.
I know that one.
I have no intention
of coming at you
with something so
obvious, Battousai.
Heihachirou Sasaki
was a good teacher,
but I've refined his techniques
with a few twists of my own.
♪
Mr. Suzuki.
(whispering)
Huh, this evening?
Everything will be in place.
Well, Himura, you're lucky.
I have more important matters
to attend to right now.
I'll have to dispose
of you some other time.
(laughing)
-Kenshin!
-Where are you?
(running footsteps)
There you are.
What's goin' on?
We were worried.
Jinpu Tai; I think
I just overheard
who they're going
to assassinate next.
(gasping)
All right, let's find
a way to stop them.
Why are they so committed
to assassination
as a political tool?
I hate to say it,
but I think it's my fault.
What do you mean?
You see, Touma's just using
exactly what he was
taught in my class.
Sensei.
What is it, Touma?
The class has heard
you've been appointed
the new head of
the Kyoto Patrol.
We're all very proud
to be students
of a such a respected teacher
of the Hino Haiito style.
The class wishes you well.
Congratulations, teacher.
Thank you, all.
What you have heard is true.
I will be leaving here soon,
and I want you to understand
why I accepted this
position with the Patrol.
Yes, sir.
Our nation is in danger
because the Royalists want
to restore their system.
They're willing to use
violence to achieve that end,
so in order to
save the country,
we must root out the
conspiracy and kill them all.
Please, Master,
I want to help.
When I'm good enough,
I want to come to Kyoto
and join your crusade.
I can't wait to prove
myself in battle.
Calm down, son,
this is no game.
You could be injured or killed.
I'm aware of that,
but I've decided to live by
the sword like you, Sensei.
I've become so good
no one is able to beat me,
and I'll only fight in
support of just causes.
What more is there
to say, Touma?
Good luck.
I used the time I had
left at the school
to teach my students
to be strong,
to be better fighters than any
opponents they would ever face.
Let's go again.
Touma was the
toughest student I had.
He was unstoppable
and completely devoted
to my technique.
But what this country needs
now is workers and statesmen,
not assassins.
Touma is a misguided kid who
was born into the wrong era.
He still believes he can
change the world with his sword.
I'm responsible, I'm the one
who taught him how to kill.
Now I have to kill him.
Sensei, you can't be serious.
You're no match for him,
you gave up the sword years ago.
-I have to try.
-Heihachirou,
you need us to help you,
and we're ready.
I thank you.
Hashizume,
is everything ready
for the assassination
of Yamagata?
It will be done tonight.
He was a good defense minister
before he started shooting
his mouth off about corruption.
He doesn't understand
the facts of life.
Money fuels politics.
How are you going
to carry it off?
The Jinpu Tai.
They'll get him on the
way home from the party.
Everything's already
been arranged.
He'll never know what hit him.
(chuckling)
By the way, how are you
going to handle the Jinpu Tai?
They're demanding
a voice in government,
you know that's unacceptable.
Don't worry, Minister,
once we're in power,
I will have them all killed.
They're too idealistic
to be of any use to us
except as assassins.
Imagine trying to end
corruption in politics.
(laughing)
Right.
Kenshin, can I talk
to you for a minute?
Huh?
Where'd he go?
Huh, they're here.
(grunting)
Sano, what's going on?
It's late and I was just
getting ready for bed.
We're about to have
some uninvited guests.
(gasps)
♪
They've come to murder us!
(chattering)
Bring my carriage around,
I have to be going.
A moment please,
Minister Yamagata.
Mr. Hashizume.
What is it you want?
Just to urge you
to be cautious at night.
I hear it's dangerous out there.
Thank you, sir,
I shall do so.
Goodnight.
♪
Goodbye, Yamagata.
(bats screeching)
♪
A new era is upon us,
and it requires men of
action to lead the nation.
I'll never become
a cynic like Himura
who wanders around
without purpose,
or like Heihachirou Sasaki
who's lost his nerve
and abandoned his mission.
I'll prove to them all
a man can change the world
with one slice of his sword.
My time has finally come.
Mr. Suzuki.
Yamagata will be here soon.
Let's go.
(grunting)
I guess you picked the
wrong house to attack.
It's too bad more
of you didn't show up.
Come to think of it,
the boy's right.
You have more men than this.
Where are they tonight?
Is your gang out there
attacking someone else?
I'm not telling you anything!
Is that right?
Let me tell you something,
Sensei's a polite man.
He won't use force,
but I'm not so civilized.
If you don't tell me
what I want to know,
I'll tear your tongue out.
(whimpering)
♪
In the name of the Jinpu Tai,
stop that carriage now!
(wailing)
Defense Minister Yamagata,
the time has come to
pay for your crimes.
Step out of that coach!
What?
You!
♪
Battousai.
Why have you come
in place of Yamagata?
A good question.
Why should I put my
own life in peril?
Huh?
I'll tell you, to open
your eyes to the truth.
You think you're
being a patriot.
The fact is you and your
friends are just pawns.
You're being used
by corrupt politicians
to take over the government
for personal power and profit.
That's a lie, Himura.
We know where
the real corruption lies
in this government.
If you don't believe me,
let's talk to the man
who hired you, then the
real truth will come out.
(laughing)
You expect me to betray him?
Listen, Touma,
you've got to believe me,
you're just a means to an end
for these powermongers.
I don't have to
listen to these lies.
Anyone who interferes with
us is sentenced to death!
(grunting)
(groaning)
(gasping)
Don't you understand?
You're all being set up.
Let's kill him!
♪
Kenshin!
I'm very disappointed,
why'd you come here alone?
The rest of us want to
get in on the fun also!
-Sano!
-Mr. Sasaki.
♪
Guess I made it in time.
You gotta stop going
off on your own, Kenshin.
I would've been very upset
if you killed 'em all.
Sorry about that.
I'm surprised, Mr. Sasaki.
What brings you here?
You have to stop this.
You're out of control, Touma.
All these murders are pointless.
It's a new era.
(chuckling)
My, my, what a touching moment
I'm faced with right here.
Two retired slashers
trying to save
their misguided colleague.
Take them all down!
(grunting)
♪
All right, Himura,
let's have it out.
I've been waiting for this
since our first meeting.
I'm going to prove that
Battousai is not invincible.
I'll bury your legend
once and for all.
(swords clanging)
(grunting)
♪
Huh?
It's something different.
Perhaps you were expecting
the Shiden No Tachi technique?
Well, I've come up
with a variation
that's even more
powerful than that.
Whatever you think
you've got, bring it on.
(grumbling)
(yelling)
(gasp)
Ni-no-Tachi.
Die!
(grunting)
I don't believe it.
How did you avoid
my new move?
It's always worked before this.
It's not a new move.
It's called Ni-no-Tachi.
Touma, it's been around
for a long time.
You didn't come up
with it on your own.
You have to strike with a second
blow when the first is avoided.
But to pull it off,
the first one cannot be so deep.
You won't recover in time.
Battousai easily figured out
that the second one was coming,
and he took the necessary steps
to neutralize your attack.
He is a student of all
the classic techniques,
something you
apparently failed to learn.
Your swordsmanship
is nothing special,
simply a tool for murder in
the hands of a common criminal.
I'm humiliated that you
were ever one of my students.
Sensei, stop.
This is the police.
All members of the Jinpu Tai,
I am placing you under arrest
for the attempted murder
of Defense Minister Yamagata.
Mr. Himura,
I must thank you again
for your help
in this case.
It was obvious these
assassinations weren't random.
They were political.
Mm-hm.
Mr. Hashizume, all the people
who were murdered were officials
who stood in the way of you
and your power brokers.
The thread running through
this conspiracy is obvious.
I now have enough evidence.
The man behind the Jinpu Tai
is you, Assemblyman Hashizume.
You're wrong, Chief!
I've never seen
these guys before.
You have no proof of anything.
I protest, you can't hold me
for these crimes, I'm innocent!
On the contrary, Mr. Hashizume.
Your fellow conspirators
have already confessed.
It's over, you might
as well give up.
No, this is a set-up,
you idiots.
I'm being framed.
Battousai, I see you
were right all along.
We were just being used
as tools in a political game.
Hashizume!
Don't!
This guy's crazy.
He's a bloodthirsty killer.
I'll tell you anything
you want to know.
I did it, okay?
I was behind the whole thing.
Just don't let him get near me!
He'll kill me!
I demand police
protection, you understand?
(chuckling)
What a fool I was.
-Touma!
-There's no other way.
(shouting)
Sensei!
Don't stop me, Mr. Sasaki.
At least I can die with honor.
I'm sorry, but it's
too late for that.
Touma, there is no honor
in what you have done.
Your pride and ambition
convinced you you were right,
and your blind obedience
has led to the deaths
of many good people.
The only salvation for you
is to admit your crimes
and accept your punishment.
In that way, at least you'll
shoulder your responsibilities
like a man.
(whimpering)
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't kill yourself.
Life is trouble, death is not.
That's your final lesson.
Let me have this.
Remember, you swore to
stop carrying a sword.
Come to think of it,
you're right.
Thanks, my friend.
Let me put this
where it belongs.
In the mud at the
bottom of the river.
♪
(laughing)
I wish you could've
seen his face.
Whose?
Defense Minister Yamagata's?
Are you telling the truth, Sano?
Yeah, of course I am.
When he discovered that
Sensei was Heihachirou Sasaki,
the former head of
the Kyoto Patrol Group,
he nearly died
right then and there.
He was petrified with terror.
It looked to me like he was
about to have a heart attack.
Am I right, Kenshin?
It makes sense, I mean,
almost everybody's familiar
with Patrol's reputation.
He probably thought
he'd be killed.
I bet he didn't believe
the man's been working
as a school teacher.
You're right, it took a while
for me to convince him.
I told him that both
Battousai and Sensei
had given up their
careers as slashers
and are devoting their
lives to helping people
instead of killing them.
Sort of a way of
improving their karma.
You know what, Sano,
you should think about
turning over a new leaf.
Your past is nothing
to brag about,
and your karma could
use some improvement.
I'd be happy to instruct--
Why, you little punk,
I oughta rip your head off!
See, this is exactly
what I'm talking about!
I think you both could
use a karma transplant.
Don't pull my finger!
Well, one thing's for sure,
everything's back
to normal around here.
♪ I sure do love my teacher ♪
♪ All the livelong day ♪
♪ I sure adore my teacher ♪
♪ Teaches me to
learn and play ♪♪
♪
(singing in foreign language)