♪
(clock ticking)
We just received
word from our scouts
that the Imperial Army
is headed here to Kyoto.
It's what we've
been waiting for.
Finally, they're
gonna come in
and remove this illegal
Meiji government.
We have to do something
to help pave the way.
You're right, but what?
We should slip into the
office of Domestic Security
and blow it away!
You can't come charging in here!
(yelling)
We have laws here!
♪
The Shinsen Patrol!
Saito, you don't frighten me.
You're nothing but
a pack of wolves.
You might as well admit it.
No matter how hard you
struggle, the Meiji Era is over.
I'm gonna spit on your grave!
I don't know how you'll
do that without a head.
What's that?
There's no way you
can win against us.
Our forces are superior to
yours in every way that matters.
We're faster,
better trained,
and more committed
to our beliefs.
When the dust from
this fight settles,
the streets will be
littered with the bodies
of you Royalist scum!
(yelling)
♪
Ahh!
(screaming)
♪
(coughing)
(whistling)
♪
Look!
They've started
shelling the city!
We've gotta find
those damn Royalists!
You'll never make it!
Leave me behind!
Forget it, that's not an option.
I won't let you die
here in the street.
I'm gonna get you to a doctor
and patch up your wounds.
By the time our
forces return to power,
you should be in great shape.
There they are!
Captain, we found two of 'em!
Damn, this is it!
We're cornered!
I'll take care of them,
you help your friend!
Kenshin!
♪
That's Battousai himself!
I'm not scared of him!
Thank you.
Cut him down!
♪
(screaming)
(groaning)
♪
So, now we meet
once again, Battousai.
I guess I should compliment
you on your skills.
It seems your technique just
keeps getting better and better.
♪
Hold it, Okita!
It's better if
you let me do this.
Don't be silly--I'm
the head of this patrol,
and I'm as good a
swordsman as Battousai.
He won't be any
trouble, trust me.
That may be, but the fact is,
you're not well right now.
You can't fool me.
You've been
coughing more lately.
I'll handle this.
Besides, I'm been wanting
to take on Battousai
since I first heard about him.
Now let's see who's
the better swordsman!
(grunting)
♪
Now say your prayers, Battousai.
(clanking)
Oh, no!
He's using the fang thrust!
(thunder rumbling and cracking)
(gasping)
It's the same old nightmare
I've been having for a week.
I don't know why
it's so persistent.
(wind howling)
And three...
and four!
(grunting)
Have you finished yet, Kenshin?
Come and play catch!
We need somebody big like
you to throw the ball to us!
I could take a
break for a while.
♪
(grunting)
Kenshin!
Grab it, quick!
Wake up, you're gonna miss it!
Huh?
♪
It's no fun if you don't
pay attention, Kenshin!
Come on, we don't have
time to goof around!
I'm sorry!
My brain must've turned off!
Kenshin better watch his step,
or those two girls will send
him to his room next time!
They're pretty tough!
Hi, everybody!
I finished my rounds!
Grandpa, Grandpa!
Have you both been good?
Did you have any trouble
with that woman's delivery?
At first, it
looked like the baby
would take too long to arrive,
but then Megumi stepped in
and administered
one of her potions,
and the baby plopped right out!
(laughing)
You have to admit,
she's a miracle woman.
She's a miracle, all right.
In honor of this
happy occasion,
I think we should all go out
to a restaurant for dinner!
It'll be my treat!
(cheering)
Yay!
So, doctor, was this woman happy
that her baby was a boy?
Of course she was happy!
Why would anybody
choose to have a girl?
Girls are noisy,
weak, and helpless.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
Of course, as a
girl, I don't agree.
You might wanna take that back
before this helpless
girl cleans your clock!
(grumbling)
All right, I didn't mean it!
I take it back!
So much for noisy,
helpless boys.
(machinery humming)
Where's Kenshin?
What's he up to?
He's just staring
into space over there.
He must have
something on his mind.
You guys go ahead--
we'll catch up.
Don't take forever.
When your food comes, I
might just have to eat it!
Kenshin?
Kenshin, are you all right?
Huh?
I must have drifted.
You do that all
the time these days.
Kenshin, what's going on here?
Uh.
♪
The Shinsen patrol?
I've been having
nightmares about them
more and more often lately.
I think I remember those guys.
They were a shadowy organization
operating outside the law.
They rooted out saboteurs
working for the Royalists!
Yes, they were commissioned
to destroy the
Royalist movement,
and they did their job well.
We battled often--
I was their archenemy.
As the years went on,
it became a point of honor
for the head of
each patrol troop
to try to defeat me man-to-man.
None of them ever succeeded,
but it didn't stop
them from trying.
I think that they're
all dead by now.
As I look back on those fights,
I realize that even though
those men were my enemies,
I didn't hate them.
We were all fighting
for our beliefs
and risking everything on
our skills with the sword.
I see.
It's pretty weird, my
going on about this stuff.
No, that wasn't in my mind.
Not at all!
What's weird is to hear
you talk about your past.
Most of the time,
I get the feeling
you're trying to forget it.
♪
Come on, Kenshin, let's go eat.
Everybody's waiting for us!
What worries me is that
I'm having these dreams now
after not having had
them for such a long time.
I hope I'm wrong,
but I think something
bad is about to happen.
♪
(indistinct chatter)
Damn, I was hoping if I got
over here at dinner time,
I could pick up a free meal.
I just hope they didn't
go to a restaurant.
If I missed the
special at Lenny's,
I'm gonna kill someone!
Good evening!
And who might you be?
I'm just an herb
salesman from Tama.
I've come to demonstrate
my latest concoctions.
I think you'll be impressed.
How are you doing?
My name's Willy Nomo.
Perhaps you'd be interested
in some authentic
Japanese ginseng.
Here it is--it's from
a root I grew myself.
Wait, you're wasting your time!
I don't live here,
I just visit a lot.
And nobody's home right now.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
Perhaps another time.
Wait a minute, Mister.
Huh?
You don't look much
like an herb salesman.
What am I supposed to do?
Wear a sign on my head?
You might as well be wearing
a sign from where I'm sitting!
Sword-fighting
calluses don't show up
on the hands of herb salesmen.
You didn't get these
from working in a field.
Who are you, and what
is your business here?
Hey, there, kid,
you are pretty sharp!
You must be Sanosuke Sagara.
I know Battousai the
Slasher lives here,
but he's not home.
I guess I'll just have to
leave him a calling card.
I figured you were
hiding a weapon on you.
I'm not surprised it's
an assassin's sword.
What does this guy
want with Kenshin?
The only way I
can protect him
is by taking this guy down.
I don't know what you're
up to, but I will find out!
By the time I'm through,
you'll be sorry you
came around here!
♪
(yelling)
Heh, sorry, pal,
that's what happens
when I put everything into it.
♪
Is that it?
I guess my informants
were totally mistaken.
They told me you had a
lethal punch, Sanosuke.
It didn't effect him at all!
I guess your
technique is adequate
for the skill level
of the opponent you face
here in the Meiji Era.
But you wouldn't have
survived for five minutes
in the Tokugawa Era.
♪
Tough luck, pal!
(yelling)
♪
How pathetic.
These dagger blades are
lightweight and easy to hide,
but the workmanship on the metal
is completely substandard.
I guess I'll have to go back
to carrying a full
Japanese sword.
Hmm?
You think you've beaten
me, but you're wrong.
This fight's just begun!
(grunting)
You're really not
too smart, my friend.
That's a serious
wound you have there.
You better give up now
before you make it
any worse on yourself.
Forget it, creep.
I'm not through yet!
You don't have a sword now,
so we'll see how good
you are man-to-man!
(yelling)
I think I ate too much.
Well, we're gonna
head for home now.
Okay, thank you for dinner!
We'll see you tomorrow!
Bye!
-Bye!
-We'll see you
tomorrow, too, Kenshin!
Come on!
You sure you're
all right, Kenshin?
(birds chirping)
I don't know what's happening,
but something's
wrong with Kenshin.
Did you see him tonight?
He just poked at his food!
He had no appetite!
You're right, I wonder
if he's sick or something.
Mm, in that case, I guess
he needs a good doctor.
Megumi, where'd you come from?
From my mother and
father, originally,
but just now I happened
to see you all walking here
when I was crossing over
from one of the side streets.
I overheard you mention that
Kenshin's not feeling well.
That's too bad, but this
would be a good chance
for me to take care of him.
I could come over and
visit him at his house.
-The poor boy.
-I hate to burst your bubble,
Megumi, but it's not
his house, it's my house!
That's a minor consideration.
Not to me!
Hello, Kenshin!
So how do you feel?
Hmm?
Oh, you really do look a
little under the weather.
Do you want me to examine
you and prescribe something?
I've just been a
little distracted lately,
-I'm fine.
-You're sure?
Mhm.
I've gotta stop drifting
away into these daydreams.
People are starting to notice!
I'm giving these
visions too much weight.
Those battles took
place a lifetime ago
and nothing has happened since
to justify these feelings.
(gasping)
What's happened here?
There's been a big fight!
I smell blood!
(gasping)
Sano!
(indistinct chatter)
How 'bout a toast, Mr. Nomo?
What--oh, excuse me, I
forgot that you prefer
that I call you
by the name Saito.
It doesn't matter.
Either name is fine.
But I have to turn
down that sake.
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't realize
you're against hard liquor.
I'm not, I enjoy a drink
as much as the next man,
but I have this bad habit.
What's that?
Well, when I drink, I
lose control of myself,
and that's when I'm likely
to find someone
to slash to death.
Over the last few years,
I found that's not
considered acceptable behavior.
(laughing)
That would get you
in trouble these days.
Right.
I have information that you
might find very interesting.
We've discovered that
Kenshin Himura is living.
He's staying at the Kamiya Dojo,
laying low and out of sight.
I tried to pay
him a visit there.
Yeah?
Unfortunately, it
was a wasted trip.
He wasn't home.
Well, I'm very impressed.
I heard you were good,
but I had no idea
you move so quickly.
I was worried you might not
be that quick on your feet
since you once led
the Shinsen patrol,
but now I have complete
confidence in you.
You should know I did some
research on your history,
and I was impressed
by your credentials.
I mean, who would've
guessed that the man
who secretly hired an
assassin like Jinei Udoh
would turn out to
be a former Royalist
and a government secretary?
These are odd times.
Not everyone is
as he appears to be.
I'm afraid I'm no longer
interested in politics.
I left all that plotting
and maneuvering behind
a long time ago.
All I want now is to sit
back and enjoy my life.
I like killing, so
being a paid assassin
is a good way for me
to exercise my skills
and supplement my income.
It also gives me a chance
to eliminate the man
who became my archenemy.
Huh?
But I've been wondering why
someone would be so anxious
to kill a reformed assassin
who poses no political threat.
Perhaps you can tell
me who the client is.
Hey, it's not healthy
to ask that question.
He's right, the
identity of our boss
will always remain a
closely guarded secret.
Concentrate on
hitting the target
and collecting the bounty.
I apologize for my rudeness.
I will ask no further questions.
You'll find we'll all
get along better that way.
Did they teach you to be so
nosy in the Shinsen patrol?
Let's face it, you
guys were a joke!
Come on, now, let's
not open old wounds.
Why don't we order some rumaki
and just enjoy the evening?
I appreciate your
offer, Mr. Shibumi,
but I'm afraid I can't stay.
I need to get back
to my real job
before my bosses get suspicious
and start investigating.
See, it would be awkward
for a man in my position.
He's an interesting character,
according to his file.
He worked as an assassin.
Then, when the Reformers
came into office,
he went underground
and reemerged
as a deputy chief of police.
He's the one that taught Okita,
who's supposed to be the
best swordsman in the patrol.
Jinei couldn't beat Battousai,
but I feel this guy can.
I think he's that smart.
I just don't like the guy.
I think he's a little too eager
to say what you wanna hear.
All I want to hear from him are
the words "Battousai is dead."
Let's withhold judgment on him
until we see if he
can pull that off.
Huh.
What an ironic world we
all live in, Akamatsu.
Here I am, a former Royalist,
hiring the Shinsen patrol
to do my dirty work.
Ten years ago, I never
would've dreamed of this.
It's hard to tell where
the lines are drawn anymore.
Is he our friend or our enemy?
I guess you're right.
We better watch our
backs with this one.
I need hot water
and a clean bandage!
I can't see the wound very
well--it's too dark in here.
Bring me a candle or something!
Yoshi, get a lantern
from the other room!
I'm on it!
♪
Oh, thank goodness.
I think the fever broke.
Is he gonna make it?
Tell us the truth,
Megumi, we can handle it!
He's going to be all right now.
But he will have to
lay still for some time.
Not everyone can survive
with a wound this serious,
but he's tough.
He'll recover 100 percent.
Yeah!
Gee, you must be exhausted.
Why don't you take a rest,
and I'll watch him for a while?
I'm all right, but if you want,
you can stay with
me and watch him.
Where's Kenshin?
That's right!
I have to tell
him the good news!
Hold on!
He's at the dojo, but
he's really distracted.
I tried to talk to him earlier
and he completely ignored me!
You should wait till
he's in a better mood
before you go there.
Right.
It must've been Saito.
He left me enough clues
so I'd know he was back.
Selling medicine door
to door is an old trick
the Shinsen patrol used
when they needed to
get into someone's home.
And the blood
tracks on the blade
indicate a horizontal thrust,
a technique that was
particularly favored
by members of that group.
Hajime Saito was the
master of the fang thrust.
I'm sure he's the
one who attacked Sano.
He was probably
hoping to find me.
If Sano challenged him, he
would've fought him for sport.
♪
I should pay more
attention to my dreams.
They're prophetic.
I imagined that Saito
holds a grudge against
me from the old days,
and he's come here
to settle the score.
I hope it's only that
and not some darker plot
I'm not aware of.
♪
(grunting)
By all appearances,
Saito's skill with a sword
is as sharp now as it was
when he headed the patrol
all those years ago.
When it comes right down to
it, I wonder if I can beat him.
And I wonder if I can
stay true to my oath
not to kill anyone.
♪
By now, I'm sure
Battousai has figured out
who the visitor was who attacked
his friend so viciously.
If I'm reading him correctly,
it won't be long before
he comes to confront me
and demand the honor of
the dojo be upheld in blood.
He'll want to make
sure I'm neutralized,
so I don't come back and
attack any of his other friends.
That's when his oath
to avoid killing anyone
will prove to be
his fatal weakness.
♪