♪
(thunder rumbling)
(rain pouring)
(grunting)
How can this be?
(thunder rumbling)
Please, I'll see to it
you get whatever you want.
Just please, let me live.
(laughing)
(whimpering)
♪
Why--I, I can't move.
(grunting)
It's time to die.
(zapping)
(rain pouring)
♪
(birds chirping)
Okay, everyone, dig in.
(blowing)
Mm, mm!
Well, everyone, how is it?
♪
You know that I created
this dish all by myself.
So, how do you like it?
(groaning)
Uh, I heard that, Sanosuke.
Sounds like you're
really enjoying it.
A lot!
It stinks.
-It's bitter.
-It's salty.
Quit your complaining, at
least we have food to eat.
There are lots of kids in China
who have nothing, now eat!
Kenshin, what are you doing?
You can't tell me you really
like this stuff, do ya?
Compared to how
she used to cook,
this food is a big
improvement for Kori.
Hasn't your stomach
suffered enough?
Why you--how dare you say
that about my cooking
when you don't help out
with the food at all!
Kenshin, get out of
the way right now
or I'll let you have it too!
I tried to warn you!
(groaning)
Please excuse me if this
visit comes at a bad time.
Wow, it's the police.
What is the police
chief doing here?
So, just what are
you doing here, sir?
First, I apologize for what
happened the other day.
Thanks, but that's
not the reason
you came here today, is it?
You're right.
Actually, I have
a special request
to make of you, Mr. Himura.
Hm?
♪
This problem we have is making
our government very nervous.
We've spent a lot
of time and energy
trying to solve this problem.
We've lost many lives,
but nothing's worked.
We need your help,
can you assist us
to stop a murdering madman
and keep him from killing?
Well?
-A murderer?
-Mhm.
♪
I told you I'd come.
(screaming)
♪
He kills with a sword, and this
murderer's name is Kurogasa.
For the last five years, he
has terrorized our government
by assassinating
high-ranking politicians,
all of whom were
former Royalists.
They were former Royalists?
He always warns us where and
when he's going to strike,
and then he does it.
He arrives exactly on time.
He makes sure that no one
lives through his attacks,
and kills everyone
by slashing them,
We have no idea what he looks
like, because he has killed
any possible witnesses.
Wait a minute, have
your people tried
just shooting this
guy with a sniper?
Mhm, of course, but this
Kurogasa strikes so quickly
that before any of our armed
body guards can pull their guns,
and get him in their sights,
he's already killed them.
Sounds like a tough problem.
Hm, sounds like he's
a former samurai.
He's probably a slasher from the
Tokugawa regime just like me.
(gasping)
This might sound sick,
but I can almost
understand how he feels.
Once you feel invincible and
develop that taste for blood,
that's a power that's
really hard to stop.
♪
Ten minutes to midnight
and all's well.
♪
(clock ticking)
Oh, it's getting close!
It's almost midnight.
He said by the time the clock
struck 12, I would be dead.
Listen, if one of you kills him,
I'll see that you receive
enough money so you'll
never have to work again.
Don't worry, Mr. Tani,
I'll get him for ya, sir.
-He hasn't got a chance.
-Yeah, I won't let him get ya.
-Getting sleepy, Kenshin?
-Huh?
Sanosuke, so why did
you show up here anyway?
Why not?
You think I'd let you run
off and have fun without me?
-No way.
-This is not some little game.
When I heard what the police
chief said about this guy,
I knew I had to come
see this for myself.
A sword faster than a gun?
Well, I got this feeling.
Do you know something
about this madman?
Does this Kurogasa
have some strange power
he's using to do this?
All right, get ready.
It's almost time.
Be on your guard, men.
♪
(rustling)
It's, it's him!
(screaming)
It's him!
I heard him attack.
It must be Kurogasa.
Whoa, he's wiped out all
the perimeter guards.
♪
Halt!
(screaming)
♪
Okay, guys.
I suggest all of us stay
here on the second floor.
I'd say he wants us
to come down the stairs.
(clock chiming)
♪
(whimpering)
You've gotta stop him!
♪
He--they must have killed him!
Heh, well, boys,
our madman is dead.
(shouting and gasping)
(laughing)
Good evening.
If you think you'll stop
me, you're dead wrong.
One, two, three.
Just 14 left,
and when I'm done,
you'll all be gone.
Hey, look at his eyes,
they're truly evil.
I'll take care of
Kurogasa personally,
and you keep an
eye on Mr. Tani.
Uh, I'll pay five
times what I said.
Whoever kills him, will get
all the money for himself,
do you understand?
-That's me.
-Yeah!
-That's a lot of money!
Don't, you stupid fools!
Your greed is gonna
cost you your life!
♪
Well, that worked nicely.
It's time.
(whimpering)
Now, for the rest of you.
(zapping)
I, I can't move.
(laughing)
(dog barking)
(snoring)
♪
He's probably a slasher from the
Tokugawa regime just like me.
I can understand how he feels.
(snoring)
♪
I don't know why.
I've got a bad feeling.
(grunting)
We're frozen in our
tracks, paralyzed!
♪
Soon you will all be victims
of your own foolishness.
Losing your lives because
you chose to protect him.
Well, I'm glad to say you
all have to go sometime.
(laughing and whimpering)
♪
I swear I'll move.
You're still moving.
Your mind is very strong.
That's why you're the
first one I'll eliminate.
♪
Just where do you
want to be slashed?
Head, arm?
It's your choice.
Nikaido Heiho.
That's your style.
It's also known as
the frozen spell.
(whooshing)
I just had a feeling
that it could be you.
♪
I heard about you in Kyoto
before the Restoration.
You can shoot chi
energy from your eyes
towards others,
paralyzing them.
They just freeze
in their tracks.
You're the remote
slasher, Jinei Udo.
And I've heard of
your exploits as well.
You, my friend, are the
legendary Royalist samurai.
I recognized you
from your red hair,
and the cross-shaped
scar on your left cheek.
You really were quite
a slasher in the old days,
Battousai Himura.
Battousai, this is happy moment
to see a slice of my glorious
past that's still alive.
♪
I've lost my taste
for killing this pig
whose been spoiled
by money and power.
There's a greater challenge
here to do battle with you,
Battousai the Slasher.
(zapping)
He's frozen.
(grunting)
You sound determined
that we have a match
with your spirit against mine.
My spirit is filled
with peace towards men,
and yours is the dark side.
Near the end of the
Tokugawa era you snapped.
You went from being a loyal
warrior to a crazy terrorist.
You became a killing machine,
and your blood thirst
was so bad you killed
friends and foes alike,
but now things have changed.
We live in an age where
we have a peaceful society,
and murder is illegal.
You must wake up
to a new reality.
Listen to you talk.
With a past like yours,
you have no room to tell me
what to do, Mr. Slasher.
-Huh?
Kenshin's not like you!
He knows what he did in
the past was really wrong!
He's chosen to give up
his samurai ways forever!
(yelling)
(laughing)
Ah!
Well, Kenshin?
(shouting)
♪
Kenshin!
This certainly is sad to see
you, the legendary slasher,
with your sword skills
reduced to the point
that fighting you is boring.
It's just too easy.
Your abilities have been dulled
by not killing
anyone for so long.
Look!
It can't be, what now?
I'm leaving but I'll
be back to fight again.
I'll give you one
day to get ready,
then I'll return to fight the
Battousai I knew 10 years ago,
and if your skills
don't improve by then,
you'd better start
planning your funeral.
(laughing)
Wait, Jinei!
He's gone!
♪
Things don't look good.
It's obvious that Jinei
means business, and through
a quirk of fate, you've become
the target of his madness.
It's all right, it's probably
best that I'm his only target.
Oh, come on.
You probably expected this
showdown was gonna happen
before we even left for
this job, didn't you?
I'd say you're right, I
really did have suspicions.
Even though I still train,
maybe I don't have a
chance to defeat him.
And yet, I must find
a way to beat him.
♪
Ten years ago, we were
both famous slashers
who had no equal.
Now, he's still at
the peak of his skills,
and I have no other
choice but to fight him.
I guess what's best is
for me to leave here
so you have time to concentrate.
Good idea, there's
just one thing.
I want you to tell
Kori something.
(birds chirping)
(snoring)
What a sight.
So Yoshi, I guess
there's a reason
that Kori's asleep right now.
Sure there is.
She was up all night
worrying about Kenshin.
Hm, that was thoughtful.
This should wake her up.
(giggling)
(banging)
Welcome home.
What a warm welcome.
Sorry about that,
where's Kenshin?
He wanted me to tell you
he's not coming back.
-Did I hear you right?
-Huh?
In order to get ready to fight
Kurogasa, he's left us.
He won't be returning at all?
If he comes back and sees you
it will be harder for him
to be mentally
tougher this fight.
He's got to concentrate on
this fight or he'll lose it.
This Kurogasa is so strong,
it's his only chance.
Kenshin wants to
transform himself
back into Battousai the Slasher
so he'll have the
skills to defeat him.
I've got to go!
-Kori, where are you going?
-Where else?
-I'm going to see Kenshin.
-Didn't you hear what I said?
He really needs to be alone.
If you find him and
distract him from his duty,
it could cost him
his life, Kori!
I hear you, but if Kenshin
doesn't come back to us,
what will happen to our
hopes for a better life?
You know, our chance
will be gone.
If he beats Kurogasa,
and I hope he does,
he'll go back to
his old samurai ways.
I am a wanderer.
I really don't know
where I'll go next.
Wish me luck.
My heart would be empty.
Just think, all of
my family is gone.
My mother and
father passed away.
I don't want to
be alone anymore.
-Kori, stop!
-We better catch her!
(dog barking)
(panting)
Kori!
Just where did she go?
Oh boy, I should've
tried to break the news
about Kenshin to her easier.
She's being so selfish.
Of course, people who
think they're in love
tend to always act selfishly.
We'd better look for her anyway.
Right now she's so crazy I
wouldn't put anything past her.
(water flowing)
Could I really defeat him?
Or am I too slow?
(footsteps)
Hey!
Kenshin!
Huh?
You are leaving?
Her anger scares me more than
the thought of fighting Jinei.
I've been told everything,
and if you're not coming
back to the dojo,
then I want to
stay here with you.
Oh, but I've gotta
concentrate on beating Kurogasa.
I know,
but I don't wanna lose you.
♪
I can't have you near me
while I'm fighting Kurogasa,
but I promise you
I'll come back.
♪
I promise you, Kori.
Here, I want you to have my
favorite blue kerchief.
♪
I wouldn't know
what to do with it.
-Just take it!
-Yes, ma'am.
I guess I just want you
to have it for good luck.
You see, I care
about what happens,
and I want that kerchief back,
so you be sure to bring it
back to me, Kenshin,
after you beat Kurogasa.
♪
Uh, sure I will.
When I win I'll
bring it back to you.
Now, you go back to the dojo,
and wait for me there, okay?
♪
You got it.
Well, now that that's over--
(grunting)
(laughing)
Kori, hey!
I hope you don't object
to me borrowing your girl.
-Jinei!
-Kenshin!
I knew this would
make you angry.
I want you to get really mad.
Mad enough to turn you
back into your old self.
Then you'll give me the
fight I've been waiting for!
(laughing)
♪
Kenshin!
(laughing)
I'll save you!
♪