♪
Himura!
Hey, Himura!
Come on, I'm getting hungry.
We should stop.
It's lunchtime, we
should eat something.
Would you answer me?
(grunting)
I won't be ignored!
Ah!
Ouch, that hurt!
Talk about close shaves.
Well, it's your own fault,
you wouldn't answer me.
That's what you
get for ignoring me
when I'm trying
to talk to you.
Who do you
think you are?
Do you think you're
better than me, Himura?
Is that what this
is really all about?
Why are you walking
through the woods anyway?
Are you really just
trying to lose me?
I'm not trying
to lose you.
I just thought it was
faster to go this way.
If we go through the woods,
we can reach the main road
by late this afternoon.
I just didn't want
to rest until then.
That's all.
If you're hungry, you
can eat while you walk,
that way we
can keep moving.
That's a good idea
'cause I'm starving.
What'll you eat?
Uh, nothing.
I didn't bring
lunch with me.
Oh, well, this one's mine
and I really didn't
bring enough for you.
Fine, I don't care.
But if you'll just tell me
about Aoshi and his friends,
I'll give you
some of this.
That's all right.
I would just love to
know what they're doing
right now, wouldn't you?
♪
And I'll never forget the
one who trained me in Kenpo.
His name was Han'nya, the one
who used to take care of me
and there was this
muscle man, Shikijo,
the fat one, Hyottoko,
and Beshimi, who was
always in a bad mood.
They were fun.
We used to laugh and Beshimi,
when he wasn't a grouch,
would tell great
beheading jokes.
Uh, what are you doing?
This snake
on the tree.
It got my attention and--
Ah, there you go again, I'm
telling you about everyone
that's important to me
and you're not listening!
That's rude.
What do I have to do
to get you to listen
to what I'm saying
anyway, Himura?
Now, where was I?
Right, I was
left alone in Edo,
remember what
I was saying?
You know about Shikijo,
Hyottoko, and Beshimi?
And, of course, Aoshi.
His image is
burned in my memory.
I remember them all as
if it were yesterday.
I wonder what
they're all doing.
Wouldn't it be
great to know that?
I cried so hard
when they left.
Himura!
Why aren't you listening?
I'm pouring my
heart out to you,
and you're over here
stomping the grass!
I might as well be
talking to a block of wood!
So just what the
hell are you doing
to those trees
and plants anyway?
Hello?
Clearing a path so it's
easier for you to walk here.
He could lose me if
he really wanted to,
but he's making it easier
for me to follow him.
You know in the right light,
he kind of looks like Aoshi,
the way Aoshi does
when he doesn't want me
to know what
he's thinking.
I should do
something nice for him.
I think I've
changed my mind.
You can have something
to eat if you want to.
I have one of these
delicious rings for you,
but you can only
have one, all right?
Hmm.
Thanks, I am
kind of hungry.
Hey, this doesn't contain
truth serum, does it?
No, it doesn't!
(audible sigh)
(cracking)
(gasping)
Hey, Himura.
I think I just
heard something.
I want you to stay
where you are.
I'm gonna go check
it out, all right?
Is it true
what you said,
that some very bad people
are trying to assassinate you?
Yeah, something like that.
If they attack me here,
Misao will be involved.
I don't want
that to happen,
but there's nothing
I can do about it now.
I'd better attack first.
Hey, hold on, Himura,
I'm a member
of the Oni gang,
I can help you!
I'm no helpless
girl, you know!
This guy thinks he can
do everything by himself.
Could you please wait up?
(panting)
(gasping)
♪
Oh my goodness.
So is he dead?
Not yet, poor guy.
Is there anything
you wish to tell me
before you pass away?
(gasping)
I realize that I'm nothing
but a stranger to you.
I will do everything
I can to help you.
Please,
help my brother
and save my village
before Shishio destroys
everything we have.
Shishio.
♪
There it is.
It looks like
he's coming to.
Who are you?
Where's my brother?
When we found him, it
was already too late.
♪
Oh, no, they killed him.
I'm so sorry
about your brother.
Can you tell us
what happened here?
What good is
it gonna do me
to tell a couple of
strangers what happened?
I may be of
some help.
It just so happens I'm on
my way to see Shishio in Edo.
(gasping)
♪
I'm from the
Shingetsu Village,
it's near here.
Two years ago,
Shishio's men showed up.
They killed the police
and took over our village.
Any new policemen that
were sent to the village
were also killed until
the policemen stopped coming.
More and more of Shishio's
men came to our village.
Our village has become
completely abandoned
by the government, they act
as though we don't exist.
They're afraid of Shishio.
♪
They left us
all to die.
That's awful.
They must be planning
something really horrible.
Won't the government help?
Your village is
still part of Japan.
I'm not so sure,
look at this map.
My brother just brought
this back from Tokyo.
Look at that.
There's no Shingetsu
Village on here.
♪
My brother saw this map
and realized that something
was wrong in the village,
so he went there by himself.
♪
He was just trying
to help his family
to see if they
were all right.
He was killed by this
guy named Senkaku.
He works for Shishio
and he runs the village.
He's a horrible monster.
♪
I have to go
back there.
My mom and dad couldn't
get away in time
and they're still there.
Not that my
brother's dead,
I have to help them.
♪
Please, brother, give
me all your strength
to do what I have to do.
You're too small
to fight them all.
I'll take the place of
your brother and help you.
Stay here with Misao.
No way!
I'm coming with you.
Stay here, I'll be going to
the village all by myself.
I want you two to stay
here and wait for me.
♪
This place is
really run-down.
He practically
destroyed it.
Shishio comes to our
village every six months
and just stays here.
I don't know why.
Senkaku controls the
village for that reason.
None of us knows
what he's up to,
just that he rules
us with an iron fist.
Shishio is in the
village right now.
♪
I have to do everything
in my power to complete
the job my brother started.
Senkaku will be
at the mansion
entertaining Shishio.
Now's my only chance
to save my parents.
Hey, lady, don't you
think it's a better idea
to follow closer,
otherwise we'll lose him.
Trust me, Himura's
a very special man.
He'll be able to detect
if we're following him.
Himura, he always has to
do everything by himself.
I'm a member
of the Oni gang.
I could help him
if he'd let me.
He is so stubborn!
(gasping)
(panting)
♪
Their bodies are hacked
just like Eiji's brother.
This is probably the
handiwork of Senkaku.
Mother, Father!
(gasping)
(sobbing)
♪
(gasping)
We don't know you,
you're a stranger.
We don't allow strangers
to live in this village.
(grumbling)
Why did you murder
these people?
Their sons tried to
leave this village.
Senkaku had them
executed for that.
Of course, we are
Shishio's gang.
(chuckling)
So we're the ones who
actually hung them.
This is a warning to others?
This is to let everyone
know this village belongs
to the great Shishio
and everyone has
to do what he says.
Anyone who disobeys
Shishio or Senkaku
will be tortured and
hung in a public square
for all the
villagers to see.
All strangers must die,
that is the law of Senkaku.
Surrender!
You surrender,
or die.
♪
(shouting)
Oh!
Stand back and put
down your weapons,
do you hear me?
Do what I say or I will
destroy every one of you.
Fine, have it your way!
(shouting)
(smacking)
(grunting)
♪
Ah!
Eiji, I know
this is terrible,
but you've got to pull
yourself together.
You can't stay
here and cry,
we've got to
get out of here!
I know you're upset,
but now's not a good time
to grieve, we've got
to get moving now.
Come on, snap out of it.
All strangers must die.
It is the law
of Shishio.
(shouting)
Uh!
Come on!
(grunting)
All strangers must die!
♪
Ah!
(gasping)
(grunting)
Uh, who are you?
I thought he was
on his way to Edo,
what's he doing
wasting his time here?
Wasting your talent on a
bunch of amateurs like this.
Does Himura actually
know this policeman?
Hmm?
Hey, Saito.
Ahh!
(grunting)
What are you
doing here?
The reason I'm here is that
one of my men informed me
that Shishio
might be here.
I decided to make the
trip and see for myself.
As a matter of fact,
I was hoping to put an army
together to meet in Edo.
The man I sent is
missing in action.
I haven't heard
from him in days.
It's his brother.
Was this boy's
brother a police spy?
This kid here?
Yeah, he's
Ei'ichiro's brother.
I sent Ei'ichiro here to do
some reconnaissance work.
But I guess that Shishio's
men found him out,
he panicked and tried
to get his family out.
These people are
unforgiving of traitors.
They must have used
his family as an example
for the whole village.
He was stupid really.
He should've just
waited for my arrival
like we had planned.
(grunting)
Who the hell do
you think you are?
How can you say that
when the man was killed?
Battousai, who
is this little...
(clicking)
...this little weasel?
What was that?
Ooh, you!
I'll kill you!
Come on, tough guy!
Hey, calm down!
He's like that
all the time,
you can't get upset
every time he does that.
Hmm.
Just forget it.
Oh?
(whimpering)
Let's take them
down from there
and give them a
proper burial.
-Good idea.
-Stop where you are.
Huh?
You can't take them
down from there.
Huh?
That is the
law of Shishio.
If you cut them down
without Senkaku's permission,
all of us will
get into trouble.
We don't know who you are,
but we have to live here
so mind your
own business.
How can you do this?
These people were
your fellow villagers,
you saw what
happened to them
and you're still
gonna do what Shishio
and Senkaku want?
How can you do that?
Because that's
what we have to do.
If any of us
break the law,
they will kill
us as well.
If we accept
their orders,
at least they
will let us live.
I don't want to cause
any more problems
for our village.
We've had enough
happen already.
Try to understand.
Now leave us alone.
(grunting)
Coward.
Calm down.
There aren't that many
people who are willing
to sacrifice for
what is right,
and even fewer that will
protect the self-respect
and humanity of others.
Unlike food or water,
you don't need
dignity to survive.
You could say
what you want,
but you don't have
to live here, stranger.
The reason we're
in this mess
is that the police
couldn't help us anyway.
(shouting)
We don't give you permission
to take down the bodies,
they stay where they are.
Now get out
of the village
and leave us be.
What?
Himura?
♪
(gasping)
Himura!
(shouting)
Who do you
think you are?
♪
(clanging)
Damn, meddlers!
Why don't you mind
your own business?
They don't care if
all of us get killed!
Ya bunch of murderers!
I'm afraid what has
happened to this village
is what is going
on in all of Japan.
In this new era, Shishio
has made these people
live in fear and he has
conquered their spirit.
The villagers are afraid
to fight for what is right.
Their fear
paralyzes them.
The only thing they live
for is just to survive.
Saito, did the government
really abandon this village?
Yes, but not
only this village,
but this whole area.
This village is now a
territory of Shishio.
I'm afraid the police
have given up the idea
of taking it
back by force.
Why doesn't the
Japanese Army just invade
and make Shishio give the
village back to the people?
Because it's only
been six months
since we fought the Seinan War.
If the army comes out
for domestic disturbances,
foreign countries would
sense the uncertainty
of the current government.
That's ridiculous, who
cares what anyone thinks?
Even if we could
use the army
to take back
the village,
I'm afraid the politicians
would not allow it.
And why is that?
Every politician is afraid of
what happened to Sir Okubo.
We could get the village
back with the army,
but it's certain that
retaliations would follow.
Politicians are
scared for their lives.
They want someone
else to handle it.
And who's going
to handle it?
Who's gonna return the
village to the way it was?
Who's gonna repay him for
the lives of his family?
♪
I will do the rest.
(grunting)
The village, the police,
the army, the government,
Shishio will do whatever
he wants with them
and there's
absolutely nothing
they can do
to stop him.
That's why they still
need us, you and I,
'cause we're slashers.
I have information on
where Shishio's hiding out.
♪
Shishio's location is a lot
closer to here than to Edo.
What do you say, Battousai,
should we pay him a visit?
Why not?
Hold on, wait for me.
No, I don't think
so, you stay here.
I have to go,
I want to avenge
Eiji's brother's death
just as much as
both of you do.
Please stay here.
No way!
I'm not listening
to you this time.
I have every
right to g--
Eiji will need somebody
in his time of grief.
(gasping)
(grunting)
♪
I'm so sorry!
Please don't hurt me!
I lost Battousai
near Hakone.
I lost him in the woods,
I'm pretty sure he's nearby.
I'm telling you,
he moves like a cat.
I promise you on my life
I'll know his whereabouts
by the end of the day.
Oh, what should we
do, huh, Shishio?
It's all right,
let him live.
I'm taking a
nice hot bath now
and I feel good.
Now go on and get out of
here and find Battousai
before I change my mind.
Oh, thank you, Shishio,
Your Greatness!
You're lucky it
worked out for you.
But if you
screw up again,
your life won't be worth
the spit on the sidewalk.
I hope you understand
what I'm saying to you.
Oh, yes, I do!
(panting)
Mr. Seta!
What's all the racket?
What do you want?
(whispering)
Yeah.
Shishio, Shishio?
What is it?
What do you want now?
I've just been
told that a man
with a cross
on his cheek
and another man
with a Japanese sword
are heading this way.
They're coming
here to our mansion.
♪
I see.
How nice of
them to come here
and pay us a
little visit.
Can't wait to see them.
Prepare for
their arrival.
Let's make sure
they feel welcome.
All right.
And have Senkaku
prepare for battle.
Senkaku is always
ready to do battle.
He loves a good fight.
♪
Now, hold on.
What are you thinking?
Just where on Earth do
you think you're going
with that sword?
To Shishio's
mansion for revenge.
What are you
talking about?
Do you want to go and
get yourself killed?
It doesn't anymore, they
killed my entire family.
I don't care if
I live or die!
I'll make them pay for
what they've done to me.
Wait a minute, please.
And don't you
try to stop me,
if you know what's
good for you.
Listen to me, Senkaku
is not the only person
in Shishio's mansion.
Shishio is there
and probably those
trained soldiers are there,
you'd be killed before you
even reached the front door.
You wouldn't stand
a chance by yourself.
You can't do it alone.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that I'm
gonna help you out.
I understand
how he feels.
If everybody in the
Oni gang were killed,
I'd want to do anything
to avenge their death,
even risk my own life.
I'm sorry, Himura,
but I've just got to
help this kid out.
You can come with me,
just don't cause
me any trouble.
(growling)
You jerk!
♪
(door opening)
Mr. Himura and Mr. Saito,
I see you've made it.
Welcome.
We've been expecting you.
♪
(chuckling)