(theme music)
♪
Lady Magdalia?
It is now time.
(water trickling)
(groaning)
Looks like
I'm still alive.
Hello!
Kenshin!
Hey, Kenshin!
Kenshin, where are ya?
Boy, my ribs are aching,
how did I get here?
(clanging)
Oh, yeah, it was
the medallion.
So where is it?
It's gotta have
fallen around here.
(audible sigh)
(grunting)
Huh?
♪
It's you.
What are you
doing here?
Hey, that should be my line.
What happened to you?
Are you hurt?
I just had a fall.
Are you sure,
you look injured.
Thanks, but
I'll be okay.
Lady Magdalia, I
brought the books--huh?
You!
I suggest you move
away from her right now.
Please, Shozo,
calm down.
He's been hurt and
I want to help him.
He's seriously injured,
he needs our help.
You just stay
out of this.
Don't worry,
I'll handle it.
♪
(screaming)
What are you doing?
Sit still,
stop complaining.
Well, it might
really help
if you stop poking
around my hand.
Boy, for a guy that
acts so violent,
you're not very tough.
I am tough, but
I'm not violent.
And could you please
call me by my name,
it's Sanosuke Sagara.
Sanosuke Sagara.
And I had to be violent
with those thug policemen
or they might
have killed me.
You don't really know me
so don't act like you do.
I think I've got a pretty
good idea what you're like.
For instance, you
often like to fight,
you eat out a lot but
don't pay the bill,
and you'd rather stay
at other people's
homes than your own.
So, I was right.
(grunting)
You're close.
Oh, you've got
another wound.
What?
So how'd you get
the name Magdalia?
I mean, is that some
kind of nickname?
How dare you, that's
my given Christian name.
Oh, well then what's
your real name?
There's no reason for
me to tell you that.
There's only one person
that knows my other name
and that's my brother,
it's kind of a
personal matter.
Sorry, but I'm not
telling it to you.
I got ya, I have this
pig-shaped birthmark
and only my mother
really knows where it is.
Oh, I gotta ask ya,
I was wondering,
what's the reason for
you being so nice to me?
It's the Christian way.
Now please put
your foot up.
Sure.
This might sting a bit.
(yelling)
I'm sorry if it hurts,
but I'm really
trying to help you.
I'd be shirking my
commitment to God
if I didn't follow the Bible
and help my fellow man.
Commitment to God?
Yes, all true Christians
are deeply committed to God
and his teachings.
Well, I gotta tell ya,
I'm just not
quite clear.
Maybe you can
help me with this.
How do you
explain Shogo?
Try explaining
the actions
of your brother
Shogo Amakusa.
Instead of
working peacefully
with his fellow man, he
tries to kill everyone
who doesn't
agree with him.
If he represents
Christian values,
how do you explain
him murdering
prominent officials and
trying to cause turmoil
for our whole country?
Corrupt politicians
are causing the turmoil.
My brother knows
that real change
can only happen
by using force.
He's helping people
save our society.
You're jealous because
Shogo is an influential man
who will go
down in history.
Well...
Killing people's not right.
Your brother has
taken many lives.
He's a fraud.
No man kills for God.
What you're saying,
I don't accept
as the truth.
Someday you'll accept it.
In Kyoto, your brother
killed three men.
Try telling their
widows and children
they were slaughtered
in the name of God.
Isn't one of your
Christian laws not to kill?
Does your brother think
he's above God's laws?
What my brother is
doing is not wrong.
♪
I have changed my mind.
Give me back
my medallion.
That medallion is
a precious keepsake.
My mother gave it to
me when I was a child.
I can't.
It's gone.
What happened to it?
I--I accidentally lost it.
Oh.
♪
Lady Magdalia?
-It's us!
-Lady Magdalia,
are you in there?
Lady Magdalia, can
you come out now?
I can't forgive
you for that.
It meant so much to me.
I can't talk
to you anymore.
It's her, it's
Lady Magdalia.
Good to see you.
Hi, Lady Magdalia.
Lady Matilda.
No, no, Magdalia.
(giggling)
Hi, all right,
let me tell you a great
story about our God.
Sounds like
lots of fun!
Excuse me,
Lady Magdalia,
I was wondering,
is God for real?
Of course.
You know, all of
us believe in God.
My dad believed
in God, too,
but bad men
still killed him.
Why would God let
that happen to my dad?
Yeah, I got beat up
by some Buddhist kids
that saw my medallion.
Doesn't God love us?
God loves all of us.
Sometimes bad
things happen
but God's grace
will protect us.
Yeah, that's right.
Shogo will build
us a country
where we can
all be happy
and live in peace.
Can he really do that?
With God's love,
it's possible.
And our prayers will
help it to happen.
We must believe that
we, through our faith,
can make a difference
in these unsettled times.
With God and
Shogo's help,
we will have our
own place to live.
Sir, this is
the opportunity
of a lifetime for us.
The Dutch have
it in their minds
to make Japan into
one of their colonies.
Shogo Amakusa will create
such a disturbance here
that taking over the
whole country will be easy.
The Dutch are receptive to
the idea of us helping them
achieve this colonization.
Very receptive.
They will provide us
with any supplies we want,
guns, cannons, manpower.
And then after we have
helped them succeed,
we will both be made rich
and powerful officials
of the new regime.
Order 20 submarines.
And 10,000 soldiers.
Shogo's popularity
has given us thousands
of new followers.
And with our Dutch friends
so keen on supplying us
and all of Shimabara
ready to fight
in the name of
Shogo Amakusa,
we'll be ready once
the supplies arrive.
I'll tell them that we
want to cooperate, sir.
Wait a minute.
I am building
God's country here,
not some Dutch colony
to be ruled by them.
I only agreed to allow
foreign involvement
because we both
believe in the same god.
We will have no autonomy
if they provide us
with the means
to overthrow the
Meiji government.
It's not worth
giving them our country
for arms or submarines.
Explain to them
that we welcome
their financial support.
But we will not allow
them to colonize Japan.
Tell them that this
will be God's country,
independent and free.
What if they
ignore our wishes?
Creating a country without
a soul is meaningless.
They will accept our terms
or we will conquer
Japan without them.
(audible sigh)
♪
(indistinct shouting)
Goodbye!
(audible sigh)
Killing people
is just not right.
No man kills in
the name of God!
♪
Huh?
"I'm sorry that
I fought with you
after you were kind
enough to help me.
I will not forget
your kindness.
Even though I lost your
treasured medallion,
I swear I will
find it for you
no matter what it takes.
Please, trust me.
I will be back
and look forward
to seeing you again."
♪
(grunting)
Just where on
this island
could Sanosuke
have disappeared to?
Huh.
♪
How are you feeling?
Were you sleeping, Kenshin?
No, Kori, I feel rested.
I've just been
listening to the wind.
Since I've lost my sight,
I feel like my other senses
have become more sensitive.
It's amazing when
we have a weakness
what the body does
to compensate.
I'm glad that you're
feeling better.
So what do you think
we can do to help you
recover your sight again?
This might sound strange
but I must fight him again.
If we fight again
and I am somehow
able to defeat Shogo,
he might in the process
manage to restore my vision.
♪
I'll have to surpass
his fighting ability
in another duel,
it's the only way,
otherwise I'll
never see again
and our country as we
know it will not survive.
But since we fought,
I keep asking myself
why the higher power
would allow such ability
to exist in a man whose
soul is so heartless.
It just can't be.
So I have to fight
him one more time,
but I can't hold back.
I have to give it
everything that I have.
But, it's just that--how
can you fight when you're...
My mind's eye
sees clearly.
It sees things as
sharply as my other eyes.
I'll be able
to defend myself.
My biggest concern
isn't my vision,
but figuring out how to
take that sad expression
off your face, Kori.
Don't waste your energy
worrying about me.
Believe me, I won't
stay blind forever.
♪
I believe you.
Your shirt should be dry.
I better go mend it.
Thanks for all your help.
That must be
Misao coming.
Huh?
(running footsteps)
I heard about
your showdown.
So, tell me,
are you blind?
(panting)
Maybe this'll make
you feel better.
Misao!
Okay, please,
stop shaking me!
So have your contacts come up
with any information, well?
Oh, yeah, now get this,
it's very interesting.
I found out
a big secret.
It's some real
hush-hush stuff
about this guy
Shogo Amakusa
and it also involves
his sister Magdalia.
Huh?
Wow.
From the look of it, that's
gotta be worth something.
Do I know them?
Those are the guys from
outside the Dutch Consulate.
Huh?
Come on.
That's sure gonna make it
easy for me to get it back.
Hmm?
Well, well, so
it's you again.
I didn't like you
when we met before
and now I'm going
to prove it to you.
No one can stop
me this time.
I really don't have
time to play around.
But, in your case,
I'll make an exception.
♪
Ha!
Damn, you cut me
with air pressure.
Fire dragon.
The wind I created
is what cut you.
I'm the only
one on Earth
who's mastered
this technique.
Well, I gotta admit
that is a really
incredible technique.
It's just a shame.
You see, I've
seen it twice now,
and maybe you are
the only one on Earth
who's really
mastered it,
but I think it's
about time I try it.
Huh?
♪
(shouting)
(grunting)
Hope you don't mind.
I kind of like to
combine my techniques.
(grunting)
♪
(groaning)
(panting)
So I guess you'd say
I'm the winner.
(panting)
Damn it, these ribs are
really starting to bother me.
This really stinks.
What I mean is I
can't breathe right.
I think I'll
take a break.
(groaning)
Hey there, you're
not attacking.
Most of the men I fight
would've killed me by now.
Always show compassion,
even to your enemies.
That's what I've learned
from Lady Magdalia.
I don't like saying this
but even with your injuries,
your punch is
still very powerful.
I'm also amazed
at how quickly
you duplicated
my technique.
You must have learned
to fight on the streets.
I've been trained by
Sir Shogo but I can't kill.
I'm afraid to take
someone's life.
I believe only
God and Sir Shogo
truly have the
right to do that.
Sir Shogo saved my life.
(grunting)
(laughing)
♪
(coughing)
(grunting)
♪
Huh?
(screaming)
♪
When I first looked into
Lady Magdalia's eyes,
I saw a place of
serenity of love.
She has compassion
for all God's people.
It took three months
of her tender care
before I could
walk again.
I never had anyone show me
so much love and respect.
They rescued me
from certain death,
and I have vowed
to serve them
for the rest
of my life.
I would gladly
sacrifice my life
for them if it ever
became necessary.
(water dripping)
I think Mr. Amakusa
is too optimistic.
He actually believes
we can overthrow
an entire government without
foreign weapons and men?
Granted his
preaching may help,
but we need ammunition.
I have worked hard
to arrange this.
If we do what he says,
it will fall apart.
That's not
going to happen.
I'll be the one heading
up this operation
so it's successful.
Now listen carefully.
Shogo Amakusa,
this child of God
has a charisma no
one else on Earth has.
He's almost God-like.
But to tell you
the truth Santo,
I've always found
that I gravitate
more to the dark side.
I'm attracted to
evil more than God.
Santo, you look as
though you're surprised.
When I met
Shogo a year ago,
I sensed this feeling
of destiny around him.
I knew I'd
found the way.
I had finally found the way
for my plan to come true.
So, Amakusa's
the lightning rod
that will give me the
power to rule Japan.
The people see this rod
and they clamber
around Shogo like ants,
ants that will do
whatever it takes
to put us in power,
ants that will
die to see Japan
made into God's country.
And that along with our
foreign friend's help
will give us more
than enough power
to rule Japan forever.
(knocking)
Yes?
We found something, sir.
We thought you might
know what it is.
Hmm?
Here, this is it.
That's Magdalia's medallion.
Where did you find it?
We found it on the
cave pathway, sir.
♪
Our Heavenly Father,
I beseech you to guide me
in a matter of the heart.
A heathen named
Sanosuke Sagara
came into my life.
He is an atheist
who does not accept
the Christian
way of life,
yet I am attracted to him.
Make me strong, Father.
Help me, I beg of you.
What's this secret you've
learned about Shogo Amakusa?
Yeah, come on, Misao.
Go ahead and tell us.
Come on.
It's something that took
place here in Shimabara.
(gasping)
(coughing)
♪
(theme music)