♪
(singing in foreign language)
Hold it, princess.
Shura, the leader
of the pirates,
was betrayed by Ginjo,
her second-in-command.
Stay away from me!
Her life was in danger
because her entire crew
had turned against her.
We don't need you anymore.
(groaning)
No!
She would've been killed,
but luckily Kenshin rescued her.
♪
(water rushing)
Well, fellas,
she's dead now.
There's no way
anyone could have lived
after falling
from way up here.
That's the end of Shura.
No one could've
lived after that.
(laughing)
But I won't be satisfied
until I see her dead body.
-Go get it.
-You heard him.
Aye, aye!
(panting)
(groaning)
(explosion)
(screaming)
(panting)
I have to do something
about her wound.
I wish Dr. Gensai
were here to help me.
Huh?
It's you.
Mm-hm.
-Mm.
(grunting)
The bullet is still
lodged inside of her leg.
That bullet has to come out,
otherwise she'll lose her leg.
(gasps)
This is your hiding place,
you're sure we'll be safe here?
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
I'll need dry,
clean cloths,
as many as you can
find, all right?
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
And I'll need some
hot water right away.
I'm no doctor, but right now,
we don't have a choice.
I'm sorry.
I just hope I'm doing
the right thing.
Hang in there, Shura.
(panting)
Sanosuke!
Kori, I'm glad to
see you made it.
Yeah, well, it'll take
more than a little explosion
to get rid of me; besides,
we have to go find Kenshin.
Wah!
Hey, Yoshi!
All right, Yoshi,
I'm glad to see ya!
Those guys blew up
the whole ship!
I wouldn't have believed
it if I hadn't seen it.
I'll get even with them
if it's the last thing I do.
Those jerks are gonna pay!
Watch it!
Hey, come on,
you better calm down,
Yoshi, before you
drown yourself.
Save some of that energy for
those nasty pirates, all right?
(fire crackling)
♪
Ooh!
Huh?
♪
There, that should
stop the bleeding,
at least for the time being.
The operation went well,
thanks to you, my friend.
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
We should get her out of
these wet clothes right away.
I wish we had a change
of clothes for her.
Huh--ah!
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
(gasps)
This place is amazing.
What a great hideout
you've got here.
♪
Huh?
Wow, what a beautiful kimono.
(bird chirping)
(gasps)
Where am I?
(grumbling)
We don't need you anymore.
(groaning)
(sobbing)
(sighs)
♪
(panting)
(gasps)
What are you trying
to do with that?
Just leave me alone!
Don't rush death.
I'm a failure.
I was even a failure as
the leader of the Sea Dragon.
I'd rather kill myself
than face the shame.
I failed.
(sobbing)
Maybe you're right,
maybe you're not fit to be
the leader of the Sea Dragon.
(gasps)
A good leader is
worried about their crew.
You still have crewmen
who believe in you.
(gasps)
♪
Sarujiro.
He risked his life to save you.
Would you leave him behind?
Leaders have more
courage than that.
If you want people
to follow you,
you're gonna have
to be brave.
Didn't you say
your father wanted
to set an example
for poor children?
The Shura I know would
stand up to any challenge,
no matter how difficult
the situation might be.
That's the kind
of leader you are.
♪
Sorry, I didn't mean to
hold your hand so long!
Huh?
You can go now.
I won't try to hurt
myself anymore.
Hmm?
-Okay.
-Wait.
Kenshin.
Did you do this?
Mm-hm.
♪
Sarujiro found a change
of clothes for you.
This beautiful kimono.
I think it'll look
very nice on you.
♪
(gasps)
Come on, you've gotta get
out of those wet clothes.
♪
Listen, Shura,
don't ever forget.
The reason that
we became pirates
was to fight our way
out of poverty.
You see, we had to
come up with some way
that we could feed
all of the poor orphans
of our impoverished
fishing village.
But don't forget,
we only attack ships
that belong to evil people.
But stealing is still wrong
and a very cowardly way
to go through life.
What I really dream about
is to make an honest,
productive, decent living.
I'd rather not
steal from anybody,
I merely want to live as a
free, honest man on the sea.
One of these days
when you've gotten older
and are ready to marry someone,
remember what I've said to you.
(gasps)
Why are you acting so
surprised about that, Shura?
One day you'll meet a man that
you'll really fall in love with.
Someday you and your husband
will take over my ship.
Iwazo.
Yeah, this is your
late mother's kimono,
I found it in my sea chest.
When you get older, Shura,
and you fall in love,
you can wear this kimono
at your wedding.
I'll never ever
dress like a girl!
(exclamations of disgust)
(laughing)
♪
(waves crashing)
(grunts)
(creaking open)
(gasps)
So, tell me, Geki,
have any of the men
found Shura's body yet?
I have every
available man
searching at the bottom of
the falls right now, Ginjo.
Don't worry, Shura's dead,
but look what I found.
Yeah, what is it?
(laughing)
Look.
That's Shura's grandfather,
what happened to him?
(laughing)
Oh, nothing much.
We gave him this.
♪
You gave him some...opium?
Ooh-wee, that stuff
works like a charm.
So tell me, have you
made any decision
about working with us, Yohi?
Yes, I have, Ginjo.
I've decided that I'm going
to work with you fellows
and hopefully we can all
get really wealthy together.
(laughing)
Glad to hear it.
Boys, put that old man in
the storeroom, all right?
-All right.
-You got it!
♪
Ginjo, the party's
ready to start.
From now on,
you're the new boss,
and we only take
orders from you.
Yeah!
Boys, I'm the new
king of the pirates.
(footsteps approaching)
(gasps)
(whimpering)
Go on!
(grunting)
Let's go and join
in on the party!
Yeah, I want to drink
till I pass out!
(laughing)
(gasps)
"Someday, Shura,
when you fall in love,
you'll wear your
mother's kimono."
"We found you
a change of clothes.
This will look
very nice on you."
What's going on?
That you, Kenshin?
I was just...
(gasps)
Sarujiro, Iwazo.
Shura...Shura, I...
Iwazo!
What happened to you?
Tell me, what did
they do to you?
Ginjo got together with Yohi.
That bastard.
They drugged me.
What?
Iwazo, did you say
those creeps drugged you?
Shura, they'll kill you
if they find you here.
That damn Ginjo!
He'll pay.
♪
I have to figure out a way
to get Shura on that boat
and get her to
a doctor right away.
-Kenshin!
-Huh?
Shura!
Iwazo!
What in the world happened
to you, my old friend?
It seems the pirates
gave him some opium.
We have to take him
to the doctor right away.
It could be serious;
let's take that boat down there.
Get going.
Mm-hm.
(groaning)
Iwazo, you'll be okay.
What are you doing?
(grunting)
(crashing)
Why did you do that?
I'm sorry, but I've got
a score to settle with Ginjo.
(gasps)
Kenshin, make sure they're safe.
This is your
reversed-edge sword.
Here, take it.
(grunting)
Now go on.
Please look after them.
Don't go alone!
I can do this!
Huh?
(birds chirping)
(panting)
Ah, we finally made it.
I'm really tired.
Now how are we ever
going to find Kenshin?
-Listen up.
-Huh?
Do you hear that
noise down there?
Sounds like some sort of a party
or festival or something.
(drums beating)
It's right near that clearing.
Let's go down there.
Maybe Kenshin's down there.
Let's go!
(drums beating)
(mumbling)
♪
Hi-ho, ya mangy sea dogs,
everybody drink up.
Let's have a toast
to our new leader.
To our new boss, Ginjo!
(cheering)
♪
Congratulations to you.
Opium, guns, and ammunition.
With that kind of contraband,
we'll be the kings
of the sea in no time!
But there's still
just one little thing
that's missing from
this party if you ask me.
Yeah, what's that?
Miss Shura.
You see that big
fire over there?
Wouldn't it be great to
burn her alive in that?
(laughing)
Yeah, toasted Shura.
I would like very much to
make her suffer some more.
Too bad she died so soon.
(laughing)
Who's that?
Huh?
(grumbling)
-Huh?
-It's Shura.
What's Shura doing here?
It's Shura!
So she's alive!
Hold it there!
Out of my way, I have
business with Ginjo!
You broke our code
by selling drugs.
You have no honor,
you have no ethics,
you are a rotten dog
to the core, Ginjo.
I am going to finish this now.
I will put an end to
the Sea Dragons forever.
This will be my last duty.
She can't do that.
Big mistake.
Huh, so you think
you can kill me.
You have good timing.
As a matter of fact,
I was just saying
how I'd like to throw you
on the fire over there.
You think you can take me?
Well, go ahead and give
it your best shot, babe.
Let's go!
(grunting)
(whirling)
♪
I wonder, if I beat him,
will the others follow me?
I'll pay you back for
doing this to my eye.
So long!
Yah!
♪
And she's tough.
That's it!
You're dead!
♪
(gasps)
(shouting)
What the?
(gasps)
(groaning)
Wait a minute,
Shura, don't kill me.
You won, all right?
I promise I won't bother
you anymore, okay?
Is it a deal?
(screaming)
(laughing)
Good job!
I knew he wouldn't let her win.
(groaning)
You cheat!
I'm a pirate,
what did you expect?
It's not important
how you play the game,
just to win at any cost.
It appears that I won,
and you'll burn now.
Guess again, dirt bag.
Huh?
♪
What are you doing?
He's alive, too.
That's impossible.
Ginjo, I had to come back here
to make sure I'd take care
of you once and for all.
(grumbling)
I'm warning you.
I'll fight every one
of you if I have to.
-No!
-Tear him apart!
(screaming)
♪
(groaning)
(gasping and trembling)
♪
-Kenshin!
-Oh yeah?
Give it!
I'll take care of you!
(screaming)
Hey, stand still!
What the?
Hiten Mitsurugi style
Dragon Hammer Flash!
(screaming)
♪
(gasping)
Damn it.
Kenshin.
Shura, take it easy now.
Are you okay?
That dirty rat.
I'm gonna blow that bastard
into a billion pieces
for killing Ginjo.
No, don't do it, there are
explosives all around here!
You could start
a chain reaction.
Quiet!
(whimpering)
(explosion)
(gasps)
Hey, what was that?
What the?
(screaming)
(gasps)
This is awful!
We've got to go there
and see if Kenshin's alive.
-Hold on!
-Let go!
-Hey, look!
-What is it?
Huh?
♪
It's Kenshin!
Ah!
-Kenshin!
-Kori!
You're alive.
Are you okay?
I'm fine,
but Shura's really hurt.
(explosion)
Shura, hang in there.
You saved our lives,
and it's our turn to help you.
I'm glad to see you, I thought
something awful happened.
It's good to see you.
Come on, there's
no time to lose.
We've got to get
out of this place.
Yeah, the whole
island's about to blow!
♪
(moaning)
It's burning out of control now.
I'm afraid it'll keep on going
until there's nothing left.
Yeah, I guess that's the
end of Sea Dragon Island.
♪
Huh?
I don't know how to thank you.
You saved my life many times.
Don't worry about it,
you saved our lives, too.
So, what do you think
you'll be doing now?
I don't know.
So much has happened
in such a short time.
I understand.
You must feel kinda like
you've lost everything.
Actually, I really do--
Wow, that's huge!
Huh?
I've never seen one
up close before.
Man, these lobsters
are humongous!
Look out!
The only thing that
really matters in this world
is having friends
and family nearby.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to make my
father's dream come true.
I'm going to live
an honest life.
I'm not going to steal
from anyone again,
and I'm going to live
at peace with the sea.
I believe in you, Shura,
I know you can do it.
Hey, Shura, I just
had a great idea.
You could come live with
us at the Kamiya dojo.
I can't do that,
because we're wanted
by the police everywhere.
Oh.
But thank you.
Kenshin, you're a rich man,
you have wonderful friends,
but then so do I.
-Iwazo.
-Yes.
We have to shove off.
-Huh?
-All right.
We have to leave now and I'm
not really good at goodbyes.
Hm.
You once said to me
that you would've liked it
if we had met as friends.
Me, too.
Let's do it.
Meet again.
As friends.
Yeah.
♪
(whistle blowing)
-Bye.
-Goodbye!
-So long!
-And thank you.
See you again someday!
Take care of yourself!
(laughing)
Thanks for everything!
♪
(singing in foreign language)