♪
(whooshing)
(yelling)
(grunting)
(screaming)
Yutaro!
(crying)
Kill him.
♪
(yelling)
(grunting)
I see now why Battousai
is considered a legend
amongst swordsmen,
but the current
here is very strong.
Even he won't be able to survive
for more than a few minutes.
Goodbye, Slasher.
(chuckling)
(birds chirping)
I'm worried.
Kenshin's not back yet?
-That's odd.
-Mhm.
I should've gone.
He could be injured or be
somewhere against his will.
I think that's him!
(gasping)
♪
It's him, come on!
Well, we got back!
What in the world
happened to you?
First, you better
take care of Yutaro.
He's burning up with fever!
Well, he almost drowned.
I worked on him till
he spit up the water,
but he hasn't come around yet.
Don't worry, I'll make
sure he's all right.
-Kenshin!
What happened out there?
Yeah, you're soaking wet!
Sorry to worry you--I'm okay.
I had some trouble.
Someone was actually
able to challenge you
on the field of battle?
I can't believe it.
Were you hurt?
Don't worry about
me, I'm all right.
Yutaro just needed some help.
He has some bad
influences around him.
Really?
♪
You're always worrying
about other people, Kenshin.
You're willing to risk
your own well-being.
You can't go on
like this forever!
♪
Very soon, our
battle will occur,
and when it does,
this house will
become our stronghold.
What are you talking about,
and who are these men?
No one here is at
war with anybody!
All you need to know
is that Yutaro put Raijuta
in charge of this house,
and everyone in it.
He'll be your master for now.
But what's happened to
the young master Yutaro?
All of a sudden,
he just disappeared!
What have you done with him?
There's something
fishy going on.
Quit asking so many questions,
or you might get hurt.
Don't worry,
Young Master's fine.
Huh?
♪
He's recuperating nearby.
We should all slip
away from this house
while we still
have the opportunity!
(whimpering)
Now you understand, Yutaro.
It's simple.
In this world, it's
kill or be killed.
It's a lesson we all must learn.
♪
From now on, you
must act like a man.
You're not a child anymore.
(grunting)
♪
(bird calling)
It wasn't long
after the Restoration
that rumors began to circulate
about a renegade group
of Shinko swordsmen
who planned to
defy the government.
Well, it is kinda
hard to believe.
I mean, a handful of slashers
trying to establish a kingdom
in the middle of the country?
Come on!
I know, I had the
same reaction at first.
But I know how hard it
is to give up your sword.
It's like giving up
your arms and legs.
I have to convince them
not to pursue this showdown
or there's going to be
a lot of blood spilled!
You're injured!
You can't just go
charging up to that gate!
He's right, and they won't
listen even if you do get in!
Gotta try.
Quit doing
everything on your own!
You always act like a lone wolf,
like no one's there
to support you.
Well, remember something:
You have a friend
to back you up.
I'm always right here
if you need some help.
Yeah!
I'm around to save you, too!
(laughing)
Hey, wait a second!
What are you guys laughing at?
Excuse me!
I made some sweets
for everybody!
Why don't you try them?
They're really my specialty!
Thanks, Hana, you don't
have to ask me twice!
Hana, have you seen
Yumi, Suzi, and Megumi?
They went out to gather
some medicinal plants!
Yoshi, don't gulp your food.
You'll hurt yourself!
Yoshi, you pig!
Oh, Master!
Yutaro!
Feeling better?
Glad to see you up!
You seem to have
gotten your color back.
Is this your house, Hana?
Why, yes!
It's nice.
It would be good if
you stayed here a while
until we're sure
you're fully recovered.
Is there a problem?
I suppose I should thank
you for saving my life.
However, I must
return to my house
and Raijuta sensei right now.
Hey, why are you acting
like such a blockhead?
'Scuse me?
Hey, kid, if it were up
to me, I'd kick you out.
But there are
some complications.
Kenshin says Raijuta's
a bad influence,
and we should keep
you away from him!
And do you plan to do
that with your bamboo toy?
You should learn
to use a real sword!
Raijuta says that's
the only true way
to measure a man's courage.
Maybe that's true
where he's from.
It's true everywhere!
Now, get out of my way!
I have things to do.
Hold it, kid, the only way
you're gettin' out of here
is if you beat me
in a fair fight.
My sword against yours.
That's fine.
Man-to-man.
This is terrible!
No playing around.
(groaning)
I hope you're ready to die.
Bring it on.
(yelling)
Huh?
Oh, my heavens!
I guess Raijuta hasn't
taught you very much yet
except for how to lose.
You're wrong!
(yelling)
I'm not done!
(slashing)
And don't plan on sneaking
out of here either.
If you wanna leave,
you're gonna have to beat me
fair and square, man-to-man.
Got it?
Wait!
I'm not through!
I haven't lost yet!
You've lost.
But look at it this way--
it's a good opportunity
to learn something.
Get away.
It's no wonder you lost.
You may call
Raijuta your sensei,
but he's never
given you any lessons
in how to use that
sword or defend yourself!
Is it that obvious?
How 'bout taking
some lessons from me?
I am a teacher of the
Kamiya Kasshin style.
Kamiya Kasshin style?
It's a kendo technique.
I think you could learn it!
You're very honest,
and you're proud.
You have the right
type of personality
to excel at this discipline.
If I do this, will
I become a fighter?
Oh, yes, guaranteed!
You'll be great!
All right, I'll give you
three days to train me,
then I'm gonna beat that boy.
Confident, isn't he?
(humming)
I'm tellin' ya, there's
nothin' better than a hot bath.
I want you to know,
in three days,
I'm gonna beat
you fair and square,
then I'm gonna walk out of here,
and you'd better
not try and stop me!
Hey, do you mind?
I'm bathin' here!
♪
Begin your sets!
(grunting)
This is easy--I'm
pretty good, right?
For a monkey with a stick, sure.
Hey, I resent that remark!
Well, you have to
develop some grace.
This technique isn't
for street bullies.
Who cares?
As long as you win.
Listen, swinging your weapon
like a caveman with a club
is a sure way to lose
a fight, not win it.
Well, what was I doing wrong?
You have to concentrate
so your movements are fluid,
like this:
And...
♪
(screaming)
You ready to try it?
♪
(grunting)
I'll be the very best!
♪
Very good, keep it up!
Ah, he seems to be
getting better at this.
I think better is an
understatement, Sano.
He's one of the most talented
students I've ever had!
Don't stop, Yutaro,
keep your breathing even!
Got it!
♪
Ready, go!
(rain pouring)
I hate to admit this,
but he's better than I thought!
(panting)
This technique sure is a lot
of work, but I have to say,
this is the best I've
ever felt about myself.
I really think
I'll be good at this
once I finish my lessons.
(thunder cracking)
And that's my plan.
It depends on you, the best
swordsmen in the country!
(cheering)
Now is our chance.
Just follow me, men.
I offer you the opportunity
to regain your stolen pride!
Trust me when I say your
sword will make you invincible!
Are you ready to destroy
this illegal government?
(cheering)
Then let's prepare ourselves
to establish our kingdom!
(laughing and cheering)
(thunder cracking)
(laughing)
The one I caught's the biggest!
No, Yutaro's is the biggest!
We'll see what happens
when everything's cooked up!
I bet you can't
eat my whole fish!
I won't eat bones!
Or the head!
It's too big for
my mouth anyway!
-What's the matter?
-Huh?
Oh, nothing.
It's just different, that's all.
I guess I'm not used to having
any kind of a family around.
It would've been nice to
have some brothers and sisters.
Hey, Yutaro, come on!
The fish is ready!
Let's eat!
Yes, ma'am!
Here you go, kid.
What's the matter?
It's not poisoned.
This is the first time I've
eaten a fish I actually caught.
I hope it's all right.
And it's the first time
you ever chopped wood
-and cleaned house?
-You're right!
And it's the first time I've
seen a human eat like an animal!
My manners are fine!
(laughing)
By the way, there's something
I should've mentioned by now
about Kenshin.
If you hadn't jumped in the
water and saved me before,
I'd probably be dead right now.
I didn't appreciate it then,
but I wanna say this today.
Uh, thanks very much.
And one more thing.
You've inspired me to
complete my training
in the Kamiya style.
Does this mean that
you'll take Kenshin's advice
and keep your
distance from Raijuta?
Why should I?
He also saved my life,
and he's promised to
elevate my family name
in the new order he
plans to establish soon.
I believe he's a great
man, and I support him!
Oh, that reminds me.
I need a bamboo
sword for tomorrow.
That's when Yoshi and I
will be having our rematch,
and I'll be heading home.
Well, I found one this
morning back at the house!
Let's go!
I'll even show you
where it is, Yutaro!
Uh...
Yoshi, don't you
wanna come along?
Nah, you go ahead.
Oh, yeah, aren't you
worried I'll escape?
Are you kidding?
I know you're not gonna
go back on your word!
There's no way
you're gonna leave here
before you see if
you can beat me!
You're right.
Let's go, girls.
You have to say
one thing about him,
he's an honorable kid.
I just hope he doesn't
get too disillusioned
if Raijuta and his
gang turn out to be
the creeps we think they are.
That's a concern.
(laughing and taunting)
Somebody's come to visit!
Sorry to bother you kids.
I'm Police Chief Maraki.
I came down here from
Tokyo to see Kenshin Himura.
It's important.
He's having a picnic
down by the river.
I heard he's
visiting this house.
Do you live here?
No, I live in the
big house up the road.
My name is Yutaro Tsukayama.
Excuse me?
That's your house?
No wonder you're visiting here!
That's no place to be right now.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Is something bad about
to happen inside my house?
Tell me, I wanna know!
♪
There's an army
battalion nearby?
They're hidden in the
trees on the property
surrounding the mansion.
Our sentries report
the troops are heavily armed
with rifles and handguns.
Damn, they're here early!
We're not ready!
(laughing)
This is what I'd hoped for!
They think they
have the advantage
because they have rifles.
Well, they're wrong, my friends!
The most effective
weapon in this world
is a trained sword technique,
and we're going to prove
it to them right now!
They're about to learn this
is the dawn of our kingdom.
The army's going to attack
Raijuta's sword group?
This is top secret.
I've told no one about this.
The government's been watching
this group for some time.
They've been worried
about its activities.
Raijuta's a subversive,
and the decision's been made
to shut the movement down.
Who made this decision?
Secretary Yamagata?
That's right, but he heard
you made contact with the group,
so before he gives
the final go-ahead,
he wants your input.
He thought you'd have
an idea of their numbers
and just how big a threat
they present to our forces.
I'm afraid these samurai
present a real threat.
They're trained killers,
and they'll fight
to the last breath.
-Kenshin!
-Huh?
We've got a real big problem.
Yutaro's gone.
-We can't find him anywhere!
-What?
Did you mention to Yutaro what
was happening at his house?
Oh, my.
I did tell him there
was trouble brewing there.
I think he's going
back to warn them.
That's bad.
You're right, Sano.
We have to catch him
before he gets hurt!
(panting)
I'm sorry, sir,
you're not allowed
to go down this
road right now.
It's by order of the government.
What's happening at the mansion?
Is anyone hurt up there?
I'm afraid that's classified.
Checking in, sir.
We've completed the evacuations.
Everyone's cleared out.
That's good.
♪
I gotta find a way to save him!
(yelling)
Open fire!
(gasping)
(laughing)
Are you surprised?
Now you know how
powerful we are!
Go before we get really mad!
Stand your ground,
fire on my order!
♪
Your weapons are no match
for the power of our Izuna.
I suppose you'll
require a demonstration.
Fire!
(guns firing)
(yelling)
(screaming)
♪
What in the world is that?
I know what it is,
and it's not good.
♪
Retreat!
We'll regroup and
attack from the outside!
Move all the injured men
and call for reinforcements!
♪
What's going on here?
I can't let them hurt him!
Raijuta sensei!
(panting)
♪