♪
Ow, that hurt!
Why are you kicking
in a sword fight?
Because I'm a ninja and
you dropped your guard.
It's your own fault
that you got kicked.
Now, I'm really mad.
No more Mr. Nice Yoshi.
Oh, so you were
just being easy on me.
Now you're really
gonna get it.
-Here I am!
-Would you stand still?
You know,
it sort of looks
like Misao could even be
a lot for you to handle.
I thought that
Misao's different style
would be a good
learning experience.
Yoshi's just a play toy
for that weasel girl.
(shouts)
♪
(panting)
Let me know when you
want another lesson.
Yoshi, you're supposed to
be the number one student
at my dojo and just
take a look at you.
Hey, that's enough!
(sighs)
That warm up was nice.
So, tell me, Weasel-Girl, just
how much longer are you going--
To be sticking
around here in Tokyo?
Don't call me Weasel!
Well, I don't know.
I do have an
open invitation.
Isn't that right, Kaoru?
Uh, well, I guess so,
absolutely, Misao.
But maybe you need
to check back with Kyoto.
Okina must be
worried about you.
No, no, it's
not a problem.
If I know him,
and do I ever,
right now, he's probably
downtown chasing girls.
Ladies.
Oh, ladies!
Huh?
How about you and me
share a little cup of tea?
(groaning)
Wait, come back!
I want to talk to you!
Do you like poetry?
How about lunch?
Somehow, I could
just see that.
Sano, that's not
very nice to say.
More importantly, isn't
there one other person
who might be waiting
for you to return?
Huh?
How about Aoshi?
Don't you think he might
be a little worried?
I don't think so.
Really, Misao?
Well, but then as
head of the Oni gang,
I really shouldn't
be staying away
from Kyoto for too
long, now should I?
I should get on
the road right away.
Huh?
Yeah, great idea, Misao.
So, goodbye already.
You want some more?
They're kinda an energetic pair,
don't you think, Kaoru?
Sometimes they
make me very tired.
Hello,
hello?
Huh?
(gasps)
Yes?
I know that voice.
It's Omasu and Ochika.
Hey, it's great to
see you gals again.
It's been a while.
Well, we're really happy
to be able to see
all of you too.
Omasu, Ochika!
Misao, shame on you.
We've been worried sick.
We haven't heard a word
since you left Kyoto.
Actually, I was just getting
ready to come back.
Is that why you
two are here?
Sure, but it's not just us.
-Huh?
Aoshi!
It is Aoshi, wow!
Aoshi.
You really made the
journey from Kyoto
to check up on Misao?
I came because
Okina's concerned.
He asked us to
bring you this.
A letter?
What?
"Sugar"?
"To my angel, Misao"?
How long are you going
to keep me waiting?
You know my heart
is pounding for you.
Every day I miss my little
flower more and more.
Come home, angel.
I sent these three to make
sure you don't get lost.
And bring me a
little souvenir, eh?
Love always, your Okina.
Ooh, that
insufferable old goat!
So, come on,
what do you say?
Think it's time
to go home yet, Misao?
Heh, so you think it
takes three other people
to keep her from getting
lost on the way home?
Maybe you should
ask for some help.
Why you little--
Come on, boys,
settle down now.
You're such
a wise mouth.
Look, shorty!
Don't call me "shorty".
Guys, guys!
Sorry, I'm not going.
What, are you serous?
I'm not going back
and that's it!
Misao!
But wait, Misao!
Oh, hello there,
I certainly hope
I'm not interrupting
anything of importance.
Megumi, come on in.
As if we didn't have enough
to deal with already.
(groans)
You'd be Misao's
friends from Kyoto.
I've heard nothing but
good things about you.
Why, thank you very much.
And Okina has told us a lot
about your medical work.
Thank you for your
devotion in helping
all the sick
and needy people.
Oh, it was nothing, really.
Wow.
Good looking,
but not too perky.
Oh, I know, I've got just
the thing to pick him up.
(giggling)
My grandmother's recipe.
Oh no, Megumi, please.
Tell me you're still
not making that stuff.
Alright, now we've all met.
Everybody please
come right on in.
Misao, stop being so--
so pig-headed.
I said,
I'm not going home.
Why Misao?
Look, I'm head
of the Oni gang.
Kaoru, is there some
reason I'm sitting here
listening to all of this?
For a problem like
this, what's needed
is some female support
instead of nosey young boys.
(crash)
Another lesson learned.
Please pardon this
little interruption.
Now, Misao, I thought
you'd decided to go home.
Misao, we're sorry,
but we thought
that you would be
happy to see Aoshi.
That was Okina's idea, right?
Yes.
So, the only reason Aoshi
came to see me at all
is because Okina made him.
That's not the case.
She didn't have to
smack me on the head.
Yeah, I mean what's the
big secret in there anyway?
Something stupid for girls.
Hey, Kenshin,
whatcha doing?
I was trying to
find something.
Did you find it?
Is it food?
No, Sano, it's not food.
I was looking for some--
Hey, if it's not food,
don't talk to me.
Hey, you're kinda wound up.
The point is Aoshi
didn't come up here
because he had a
desire to see me.
Misao, I think you're
wrong about that.
It's obvious he
really is concerned.
She's right.
He'd never
say it out loud,
but Aoshi
worries about you.
Oh, really?
All this just because the
man she's got a thing for
came up for business
instead of personal reasons?
Hey, be nice.
Yeah, right.
Listen here!
I'm not a
teenager anymore,
I'm a woman with
a woman's feelings.
Yeah, you're right.
Sometimes other people
just don't seem
to notice when a girl
is all grown up.
(gasps)
But my impression
of this guy is that
he wouldn't do anything
unless it was something
he really wanted to do.
That's it exactly.
All this time he's never
bothered to come up to Tokyo
but now suddenly he does
and he comes here
to see Misao.
Don't tell me that doesn't
mean something good.
That's an excellent point.
I would say,
she's right.
♪
There's hope,
can't you see that?
Hmm.
I guess I could
go back to Kyoto.
If I had a good reason.
You do, Misao.
You know, we can leave
right now if you want to.
Wait a minute, you don't have
to leave right this second.
Why not at least do some
sight-seeing while you're here?
Learn a little bit
about Tokyo.
You think we should?
Great idea!
I still need a
souvenir for Okina!
And an all-girl shopping trip
could really be a lot of fun.
I will be going
back with you,
but we're going into town first
since I need a gift for Okina.
We'll be back before dark.
I just don't get it.
First, she's going,
then, she's staying.
Then, she's going again.
Then, tomorrow
we'll get a fresh start
and we'll all
leave for Kyoto.
I'll see you tonight then.
Right, this'll be fun.
Kenshin, you're in charge
of the house, alright?
I'll try not
to destroy it.
Alright, tell me again,
why I'm going with you.
The more the merrier.
Pick up your feet.
At last, it'll be
quiet around here.
I smell something.
Huh, what's that?
I suspect this is an all-girl
plot to get rid of the men,
and once they get
to Tokyo, they're free.
They're going to have
a complete female feast
while we're
just left behind.
How evil!
There's no way we can
allow them to get away
with this
conspiracy of females.
We have to stop 'em.
We've got to
catch 'em red-handed.
Let's do it.
-Come on.
-Right!
Finally, things should be a
little more relaxed around here.
Yes?
The perfect opportunity for us
to fulfill that promise we made.
What promise is that?
When I was in Kyoto,
we promised to do this.
We said we'd share a
traditional tea ceremony.
Yes, now I recall.
♪
I thought the temples
at Kyoto were spectacular,
but look at these.
Beautiful, huh?
Following these women is
starting to make me hungry.
Yoshi, let's eat.
They're getting away!
♪
Please let Kenshin
know how I feel.
Please let Aoshi
see me as I am.
Please cure Okina's
lecherous ways.
Please let me see
Seijuro Hiko again someday.
Please let Sanosuke
get some intelligence.
He could really use it.
♪
(sneezes)
Quiet, they'll hear us.
Sorry, Yoshi, I guess
I must have hay fever.
Misao, what did
you wish for?
It's secret.
What did you wish for?
Mine's secret too.
(both giggling)
Hey, let's all go
get something to eat.
Can't go shopping on an
empty stomach, you know.
Mm-hmm.
-Mm-hmm.
Thank you, Aoshi.
I really don't
know the ceremony,
but I'm glad we
have the opportunity
to keep the promise
we made to each other.
I'm sure you'll
do a fine job.
On a way to see how
a friend may have grown
when you weren't
aware of it.
I wonder.
Does candy go
well with tea?
There's no sweet cakes,
but maybe this will do, huh?
This looks good!
We gotta stay
close to them.
Come on!
Sweet cake for me!
Adzuki bean soup.
I'll have some salad, please.
I'm gonna try the
sweet potato bean curry.
I'm having sticky rice
and honey.
Just look at this place.
No one here but women.
Tae, Tsubame!
(groans)
Kaoru, what a surprise!
Out sight-seeing?
Yes, for a change, and you?
It's my day off today,
but we really like
the sweet cakes here,
don't we, Tsubame?
Mm, you bet!
Where's Yoshi?
It's just us
girls today.
Why don't you
sit with us?
Great, thanks!
Tsubame's in on it too!
Seems like they
come here a lot too.
It's worse than we thought.
We'd better watch 'em.
Aoshi?
Yes?
Do you really enjoy this?
Yes, I do.
A realization
is coming to me.
I'm getting a cramp.
(groans)
Oh, Miss,
another order, please!
Uh, Kaoru, dear.
Huh?
Maybe you should
think about it
and cancel the next order.
You do look a little heavier
than the last time I saw you.
Thanks for your
concern, Tae.
Kaoru, Tae is right.
You really like
how Kenshin cooks.
You don't want to be a
sumo wrestler, do you?
(growls)
Kaoru, honey, I'm
only thinking of you.
You can't afford
to let yourself go
just because you've
got a man in the house
and he feeds you too well.
You'd better consider the
wisdom of a diet, young lady,
while it might still
make a difference
in what we'll laughingly
call your love life.
Huh?
I'd go on a
diet for Aoshi,
if that's what he
wanted me to do.
Misao, honey, you'll never
have to worry about that.
Huh?
Trust me on this.
You have the body
of a little boy.
What?
How can you
say such a thing?
(women laughing)
What?
Oh, sorry.
But Misao, I'm sure you'll
get the figure you want
before much more time goes by.
I think you just need to
be a little more patient.
You know, I was skinny all
through my early 20's as well.
Huh, 20's?
Twenties?
But I thought-- oh!
Is that what
everybody thought?
Misao,
the 12 year old.
The leader
of the Oni gang
and they all see me
as some little kid?
I'm a fighter!
I'm supposed to be slender,
so I can move!
A big chest would
just be dangerous,
but the body
of a little boy?
Well, I've never had to deal
with this problem myself,
since I've always
been fortunate
in the figure department.
But let me give you a
little womanly advice.
Nutrition is
very important.
We need calcium.
Make sure you
drink milk every day
if you want an
attractive figure.
Honest, will
that really help?
Oh, yes, and to
promote your metabolism,
you need to
exercise and sweat.
Yes, and what else?
And I've always found
that a daily invigorating
massage is also helpful.
Massage, got it.
And make sure you whip
yourself with willow branches
to increase blood circulation.
But what if I don't
have a willow tree?
Well, then jump from
hot water to ice water,
over and over again.
Oh.
Is doing a little shopping
appeal to anyone else?
Of course, it does,
Kaoru, but first,
one last piece of
advice for Misao.
Just in case all
those other methods
don't work for some reason.
Here's what you do.
What's that?
Go out and
find someone
who doesn't
want you to change
because he likes you
just the way you are.
(groaning)
Oh, that's better, thanks.
There are thousands of nerve
endings in your feet, Kenshin.
Oh, this is so cute!
-Oh, yes!
-Let me try it on.
That looks
great on you.
Well, what
do you think?
(whistles)
I don't think we need
to follow them anymore.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
(grunts)
Huh?
Tsubame, you all right?
See that guy
in the green robe?
Go get him!
Uh, what exactly are
you doing there, Himura?
Some people
call it laundry,
and I try to get mine
done almost every day.
So, you do this voluntarily?
Only if it's not raining,
otherwise it won't dry.
You wash clothes?
I'm just a
wanderer lucky enough
to be given lodging here,
so I try to help out
in any way that I can.
They're good people,
and this is honest work.
Kenshin, come play with us!
Yeah, play a game!
Just a minute, you two.
Can't you wait until
I get this laundry done?
Come on,
play with us now.
Yeah, play now,
work later.
(chuckling)
Aoshi, Aoshi,
come on, let's go!
(laughing)
Hey, come on, play!
♪
(snickering)
Should be safe
enough here.
You really think so?
Huh?
Who are you?
You can't get away
from the Oni gang!
Huh?
Let's talk about it!
(yells)
(screams)
Tsubame, they're back.
Wha--?
Hey, here you go.
Oh, thanks Misao.
The thief?
I wouldn't worry about him.
He's probably hanging
around somewhere.
Now just where could
that guy have gone off to?
Sano, you'd
better come here.
♪
Wow-wee, those
girls are serious.
No kidding.
Hey, you two.
What're you doing?
Oh, no,
it's the police!
What're we gonna do?
Run!
Right!
Hey, you two!
Come back here!
(groaning)
That wretched girl.
She's gonna
pay for this.
Wow!
-A crane!
-That's beautiful.
Could you make me
one of those please?
Sure.
That's great, Aoshi.
I never knew you could
be so good with kids.
I used to make these for
Misao when she was young.
(giggling)
You obviously care
a lot for Misao.
Your feelings for her
run very deep.
Both of Misao's parents were
murdered at an early age,
and so I was her guardian.
Do you still think
of her as a child?
Misao has grown up now.
She's a young woman,
lovely and strong.
(both panting)
Those police
don't give up.
Then, why do they have
to chase us anyway?
We didn't do anything.
We're totally innocent.
(men yelling)
Hey, it's him.
Our turn to shine.
Fortune finally
smiles on us.
Not much of an opponent,
but enough to get
some good practice on.
And practice makes perfect.
Hard crackers, please.
Do you like the
black purse better
or do you like
the white one?
Well, if you can't
make a decision.
Yeah?
-Get both.
-Right.
Oh, I can't wait
to taste this sake.
Ladies,
if you don't mind,
we'd like your
attention over here.
In fact, we insist.
(both groaning)
You just won't give up.
Want us to
write this down?
You've got a
lot of nerve!
I'll say
that much for you.
Coming into our town
with your silly trick moves.
You're gonna
get a spanking.
"Silly trick moves?"
"Spanking?"
Would you get out
of the way, please?
I'm not through shopping
and there are
still some stores
that I haven't been in yet.
Ah, well, you're a
nice piece of merchandise.
Do me a favor
and don't touch me.
Don't make me mad.
Yeah, what's
gonna happen?
(grunts)
(groans)
My goodness, these crackers
are harder than I thought.
Now you've done it!
Let's get 'em, boys!
May I borrow
this please?
I'm a woman,
hear me roar!
(shouting and yelling)
Quiet now.
I think the ladies
could be returning
from their trip to
town at any time.
Shall we go for a walk and
join them on their way back?
A walk sounds pretty good.
It is a nice day.
Missed our chance again!
Looks like we're
a little too late.
(groaning)
-Women.
-Scary.
Hey, you two!
Hold it right there!
-Run!
-Again?
You come back here.
Right now!
-Wait, no, we're--
-Innocent!
Hello!
♪
Hey, we're back!
Welcome home, ladies,
I hope it was a good day.
Oh, yes, a lot of things
turned out just fine.
One of the greatest
pleasures we have
is remembering good days.
Kenshin, you're right.
(blowing air)
Yours,
souvenir.
A paper balloon?
You bought me one just
like this a long time ago.
I just felt like
returning the favor to you.
You know, you haven't
changed a bit, Misao.
Actually, Aoshi, I did.
When you weren't paying
attention, I grew up.
♪
I'm a woman.
We could talk about
that if you like.
♪
Yes, I'd like that a lot.
Kenshin, there's
something really different
about Aoshi from this morning.
Well, it could be
that his vision's
become a little
more contemporary.
Hmm?
(panting)
-Sano!
-Yoshi!
Where have
you two been?
Why were
you running?
Are you all right?
No.
Not really.
Something's
not right here.
Are you hungry,
Sanosuke?
Here's some hard
crackers to nibble on.
No, no thank you.
Oh, you poor baby.
You must have
a bad tummy ache.
I'm fine.
Tomorrow,
we go back to Kyoto!
-Oh!
-What's the matter?
In all the excitement,
we forgot to get
Okina's souvenir today.
Oh, no.
Well, we'll just
go back tomorrow
and get one for him.
-No!
-No way!
Why on Earth not?
Because, Kaoru, nothing good
comes of these trips to town.
What do you mean?
What did you do?
Nothing!
Why don't I believe you?
Tell me what you did.
I did nothing, I swear.
I'm innocent.
We weren't following you.
Come on, tell 'em Yoshi.
Tell 'em!
♪