♪
In 1602, the water
and wind families fought.
They wanted to control
the flow of ki.
According to feng shui,
the elements
must be in harmony
or disaster will strike.
Do you have any
word on their position?
Water is aligned
in star formation.
It could be
very dangerous!
(screaming)
Hold your ground!
We can't let wind
out maneuver us!
We must hold on
and stay together.
♪
The ki force
has been unleashed.
What are we
going to do now?
(breathing heavily)
Let's head
for the shrine.
♪
(wind whistling)
Listen to me, water.
Only one of us
can control the ki.
We are more powerful
than you are.
You will never be able
to defend yourself against us.
Surrender, or we
will take this shrine.
Our future in Ito
will be uncertain
if you don't surrender.
The harmonic balance
will be disturbed
and misfortune will reign.
All of your ki
to us or I promise,
we will destroy
your entire family.
♪
Sir, you'd better take
a look at this immediately.
We have succeeded in
counteracting their strategy.
Feng shui has shifted
the balance to our side.
The ki flows with us.
♪
(screaming)
Water!
Have you had enough yet?
(men screaming)
Ki is a double edged sword
that will conquer
those that are weak.
We, of the wind family, will
not allow water to prevail.
We'll fight this
battle with our lives
if it takes every single
ounce of our strength,
and when this
conflict is over,
we will rebuild the
shrine in our image.
I promise you!
(men yelling)
Answer me, water.
Will you quit now or are you
ready to meet your maker?
♪
We will retreat for now!
Let's go, men.
Hear me, wind family,
we will come back
to this land someday.
It may not be
tomorrow, or the next,
but perhaps when your
grandson is old and grey,
and we promise to
return with a vengeance.
Just wait and see!
♪
Two hundred and seventy-five
years passed by.
Since the time of the battle
between wind and water,
the elements have
remained fairly stable,
but recently a
spark of dissention
has become noticeable.
Incidents have
occurred that seem
to be slightly askew
and the appearance
of a mysterious stranger
has sent the town
into a flurry of concern.
People have become uncomfortably
apprehensive and curious,
not knowing where to turn.
This leaves questions
that need to be answered.
What caused these events
to happen and why?
Is something
the matter here?
The water's evaporated
from the well.
It's all gone.
It was completely
filled up until yesterday.
Now there isn't a single
drop left for us to drink.
That's strange.
I think it might be
some kind of a curse.
-A curse?
That's right.
As a matter of fact,
a boy was injured
while swimming about
three days ago,
and the next day,
Amora, the carpenter,
fell right off of his roof.
There have been all kinds of
bad things happening in town.
It's very strange.
Right this way.
-Hmm?
It's over here.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Huh?
♪
I found it.
This section
of the street
is stopping the flow of ki
and causing the trouble.
It is?
Yes.
If you don't do
anything about it soon,
there are certain
to be more disasters.
What can I do?
I can't put all of these
people out of business.
(gasps)
♪
What do you want?
Hurry up, Kenshin, all my
clothes are getting soaked!
I'm trying.
Well, move a
little faster!
I'm doing my best.
(growls)
This rain is just
passing through.
It should be over soon.
She's upset because she
got her fancy underwear wet.
Now she'll have
to wash it all again.
(groaning)
What's the big idea?
Yeah, keep your
clothes to yourself!
I'm not in charge of it!
You lazy bums!
Get off that porch
and help me out,
or I'm going to make
your chores so awful,
you'll beg me to
bring in the wash.
Hmm?
Huh?
-Huh?
Whoa, the water's red.
Whoa!
Enjoy your
wind chime, sir.
Huh?
Thank you for
your help, sir.
I was very worried
about this situation.
We were just lucky
that a feng shui master
happened to be around to check
the area for disturbances.
Now we'll be able to
take care of the problem
before something
else happens.
Ladies, were there any
more strange incidents?
-Hello.
What a handsome
looking man.
What's your name, sir?
My apologies.
I am Tsunan
Tsukioka.
I write articles and
publish my own newspaper.
I heard some strange things
were happening here.
Can you tell me
anything unusual
you might have
noticed please?
It's all been taken
care of by that nice man.
The house that was there was
unlucky so it was destroyed.
He put a stone
in its place
to repel the evil
and bring good fortune.
If the house
was destroyed,
then what happened
to the tenants?
He bought up the land
and all of their property.
They were grateful to him
because he paid a good price.
He paid for their
moving expenses,
so they left
town right away.
(laughing)
He's so nice.
It's very hard to believe
that such a wonderful
man exists in this world.
What's his name?
Yunoshin Saeke.
He's president of
the Saeke company.
Yunoshin Saeke.
I just don't understand
what could have caused this.
Our water has
been undrinkable
for over three days.
I wonder if this happened
to our neighbors.
No one's reported
anything that was unusual.
Maybe you went
and did something bad
that made the
well got mad.
Sano, don't even
say a thing like that!
Hmm?
Look who's here.
You made it.
It's Tsunan.
Sano came to
town and told me
about the problem
with your well.
Would you mind if
I take a look at it?
♪
So, you say they had
to destroy the house?
Yes, but that wasn't the only
incident that's occurred.
I've heard of
several other events
that seem strangely similar.
What gets me
is every time
one of these
weird events occurs,
a feng shui expert
suddenly appears
followed by a businessman
named Mr. Saeke.
He gives them some money
and then destroys
the building,
so there won't
be any bad luck.
So, that can happen to us?
It might not be a
bad thing after all.
We can get
a lot of money,
and then we can use
it to build a new dojo.
Besides, having my own
room would be wonderful.
Don't be an idiot!
I'm not selling
off my property.
It belongs
to my family.
Tsunan?
What about this man?
I've been trying to gather more
information about him, Kenshin.
As far as I know,
he's a powerful man
that has made a fortune in sea
transportation and real estate.
He's also become
known to the community
as a praise-worthy
philanthropist.
Huh?
What is it, Kenshin?
Hmm?
What if he's
the feng shui guy?
♪
Need any help?
Not from you!
You can't just
come over here
and make us
give up our dojo.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Huh?
How'd you like a punch?
Let's just hear him out.
There is poison air
coming from the south.
It's effecting the
well water in this area.
So are you a practitioner?
Get out!
♪
I want to apologize
for my intrusion here.
Goodbye.
♪
Tsunan, do you
think that guy
was the feng shui expert
you were talking about?
I've never seen
that man before.
Too bad,
I want my own room!
Don't mention
that again!
Hmm.
(electricity crackles)
♪
Good heavens!
What's going
on out here?
(gasps)
♪
(whimpering)
(energy pulsing)
Listen up, men.
We're making some headway
in this investigation.
The scandalous allegations
that we've
managed to uncover
are rapidly becoming
front page news.
Several men have
been accused of bribery.
Thos participating in
this offensive behavior
have included minor officials
as well as senators.
We will be judged
on our ability
to successfully bring
these men to justice.
Are you with me?
-Yes!
Good, then I suggest we make
this our number one priority.
Um, sir?
(sighs)
Excuse me.
Is this important?
Can't you see
I'm busy right now?
Have you heard
about feng shui?
The problem is
getting troublesome.
I'm aware of it.
But, we're very busy.
With money moving from the
public to the private sector,
the government's
losing a lot of control
and corruption's rampant.
Money is moving freely
through the cabinet
without the proper
authorization.
So, we can't afford
to waste our personnel
on some
superstitious nonsense.
I respect your--
(knocking)
What is it?
I'm sorry to barge
in on you, sir,
but this is very urgent.
I'm delivering a message to
you from General Yamagata.
It's important that
you read it immediately.
Thank you,
you're dismissed.
Thank you, sir,
and good day.
Hmm.
What is it?
He wants me to come
and meet with him
the day after tomorrow,
but I have no
idea what for.
I can't believe
I have to do this
when we're
inundated with work,
but he leaves
me no choice.
What could be
so important
that he'd have me
leave my post?
I'm scared.
What are you
worried about?
It's just that-- hmm?
Huh?
(clears throat)
Can I help you, sir?
I'm a feng shui master.
You are?
That's right.
I'm here to inspect
your establishment.
I found that there's a
disturbance in the ki force.
Huh?
If you don't do
anything about it,
you're gonna have a
disaster on your hands.
Uh, the kitchen's over there.
Huh?
You can't just-- hey!
Come back.
Huh?
Your setup
here is bad.
Oh.
The elements don't work
in harmony in this kitchen.
You can't boil water in
this spot, for example,
because it's not
compatible with the wood.
Who is this
troublemaker, Tae?
Get him out of here before
I punch him in the nose.
He's interrupting our work.
Just ignore him.
We've never had anything
bad happen here before.
You're spouting nonsense.
I'm telling you, Miss,
you have to remodel
the entire kitchen.
(yelling)
(frantic yelling)
Oh, this is horrible.
My restaurant,
we've got save it.
Please, or
I'll be ruined.
Oh, it's too late.
Wow, this
place burned up
like one of
Kaoru's suppers.
Oh, well, at least
it's fortunate
none of the neighbors
houses caught on fire.
Some people think this
place has evil spirits.
That means I won't be able
to do business here anymore.
-Oh!
-Don't worry, Tae.
We'll help you
get through this.
I don't like
what's going on here.
I want to find out some more
about that feng shui guy.
From the way
that Tae described
his face and appearance,
I'd be willing
to bet that he's
the feng shui expert
that our friend,
Tsunan, had
talked about.
Is the owner here?
That's me.
May I come in?
Yes, please.
My name is
Yunoshin Saeke.
I'm the president
of the Saeke company.
Someone informed me
that you had a big fire.
I'd like to buy
you a talisman stone
to put on your property.
But why?
It's for good luck,
and it may improve
the flow of the energy
in this area if you
choose to move out.
I don't want to!
Sorry, I apologize for
coming here unannounced.
It was extremely rude of me.
Perhaps, I should
come back another time
when it's less hectic.
It's not my nature
to sit around
when I know that
others are in pain.
I appreciate your concern,
but I'm much
too busy right now
to give it much thought.
Come back at
another time
and we'll talk
about it then.
Okay, I'd be happy to
help you out in any way,
so don't be
afraid to speak up.
Being able to help
people achieve happiness
and prosperity is a very
pleasurable experience.
-You're a fraud!
-Huh?
That was mean!
I think that he's
trying to trick you, Tae.
No, I'm just
trying to help.
-I'm an honest man!
-Shut up!
We've heard all about you
and the way you've been
buying up everybody's
property around here.
(growls)
You've got
it all wrong.
I've never forced
anyone to sell anything.
If you were a smart guy,
you would high tail
it out of here
before I throw you out.
I'm very sorry to
have bothered you, Miss.
Just know that
I'm here for you
if you decide to
change your mind.
He'd better not
try coming back.
Tell me, Sano,
who was that man?
This makes the
formation clear.
It's pointing
towards northwest.
The flow of ki was
strategically designed
in a star shaped pattern.
(energy pulsing)
Now, I'm beginning
to understand.
Mr. Koachi, I want you
to listen to me carefully.
Don't underestimate
the power of feng shui.
It is a proven method
of domination
that has been used by the
Chinese for thousands of years.
The Qin dynasty
fell apart because of it.
It's all a bunch of hogwash
if you're asking me.
I disagree
with you on that.
It can be used as a weapon,
and that's why
the Qin dynasty failed.
Sometimes it can be
helpful if it's used
to enhance the quality
of people's lives,
but often times, it's not.
Excuse me, sir,
I'm about to close in
on the biggest
case of bribery
that's ever been uncovered
in Japan's history.
I don't have
time for this.
All this malarkey sounds
very frivolous to me.
I would respectfully request
the next time
you ask for me,
it's something
worthy of my time.
Chief.
Since Mr. Koachi is up to
his neck in bribery cases,
perhaps, you'd be
more interested
in heading up this
investigation.
Yes, sir.
You can't do that!
I'm in charge!
I'll have to
handle this.
The Ministry of the Army
has been taking
this matter seriously,
unlike the
police department.
Ever since we sent
our troops to Kagoshima,
we haven't been able to
rebuild our forces enough
to withstand another attack.
We must find a way
to strengthen our position,
or we wont be able to
ensure the security of Tokyo.
That sounds
pretty ominous, huh?
That's a bit of an
overstatement in my opinion.
(laughing)
You're acting like a
superstitious old fool.
You're the one who's
being ignorant, Koachi.
Feng shui is a powerful
force to be reckoned with.
If you aren't going
to take this seriously,
then I'm going to start
my own investigation.
Then you are mad.
You're abusing the
power of the military
by carrying this out.
I cannot believe you want
to humiliate the
army in this way.
And I'm not going to let the
police department lose face
if I have anything
to do with this.
In fact, if anyone
in my department
even touches this subject,
I am going to
have them fired,
do you understand?
(chuckles)
What's wrong?
How come you're only eating
the ones on that side?
I made this batch and
you haven't touched one.
They taste awful,
that's why.
(screams)
Thank you all for bringing
this food over here.
Have you decided
what you're going
to do about the
restaurant, Tae?
No, not yet.
I mentioned what happened
at the restaurant
to our friend, Tsunan.
He's been investigating
the situation.
Maybe he's got
some new information.
It wouldn't
hurt to ask.
-Hello again.
-Huh?
I was hoping that
I could visit.
What are you
doing back?
I was wondering if things
had calmed down a little
so we could talk.
I'm not giving up my business,
if that's what you want.
We've had this
area completely tested.
If you leave the
situation untreated,
I guarantee that something
horrible is bound to happen.
I can pay you a good
price for the property.
You can move and you won't have
anything more to worry about.
What do you think of that?
Huh?
Thank you so much
for your concern,
but I love
this restaurant
and have no intention
of leaving.
Please leave this place.
There is no more
you can do for me.
I've made my decision
and now I'm going to have
to deal with it alone.
Go away.
Forget we ever met.
I'll take my chances
and hope for the best.
(growls)
It's just too bad.
I hope you're right.
I'll be going now.
In the meantime, I'll
leave you my blessings
for your happiness
and good fortune.
Goodbye for now.
It's over.
Why'd you have to bow
down to that big creep?
You should have just kicked
him out on his butt.
I couldn't.
She has self-control.
I would have
slapped him silly
the minute he walked
into the restaurant.
Yeah, Kaoru's not happy
unless she's slapping
somebody around.
Oh, come on, she's not
really like that, is she?
Tae behaved in a manner
that was befitting
a professional
business woman.
I applaud your spirit.
Sano, would you
quit teasing me?
I mean it,
you did a great job.
At least he's gone.
Yeah.
♪
(growls)
Well, we have
to get going now.
We'll drop Tsubame
off on our way.
Take care, and
don't worry so much.
Huh?
Watch out!
Everybody get back!
(yells)
(shouting)
Who are you?
(grunting)
Oh, my, what's
the matter with you?
My body won't move.
I'm frozen.
(grunting)
Kenshin, you've
got to try harder.
You can't just
stand there.
(grunting)
Kenshin!
Oh no!
(breathing heavily)
♪
(shouting)
Oh.
(gasps)
(groaning)
Go find a
safe place!
Alright!
Kenshin.
What happened to you?
(coughing)
♪
(panting)
Who are you, huh?
♪
Jinpu.
I'm here...
♪
to save you from
being destroyed.
♪
I'll be!
It's the star!
♪