(theme song)
♪
(maniacal laughter)
(chanting)
Jinpu!
(zapping)
You can't fight Tang shui.
Ha!
I need to see the Commander.
Hey, who's out there?
Please listen.
Kanaji's shrine was
a principal point of ki
that was built to
protect the city of Edo.
When it burned down
during the the Uno War,
the flow of ki was
weakened considerably.
The shrine was designed
in a dragon formation,
with the head being
the grave of Tokugawa's.
It was located at
the northeastern section
of the shrine.
Its unfortunate destruction
made it impossible
to restore the formation
to its original power.
We've tried to do
the best we could,
but it has never been
the same as before.
We've used sand
to simulate water.
It hasn't been as effective
as the actual spring
located at
the throat of the dragon.
We hope this will quench
the dragon's thirst.
You're finished with most of it.
What more needs to
be done, old man?
You've given the dragon
a head, a throat,
and four limbs.
It's complete.
No, it's not.
It doesn't have a heart.
(grunting)
I don't think this door's
been opened for years.
♪
Oh, it smells musty.
Ugh!
What's that?
It's a dragon sculpture.
-It used to be in the spring.
-Ugh!
The Master Jingoro
Hidari created it.
We can use it to
complete the formation.
It will be a good
substitute for the heart.
♪
(chanting)
You're late coming.
I came as soon as I was able.
There's not much time
before the ki passes
through this place.
♪
This is weird.
Tang shui.
We've found Reisui.
♪
They appear to be sitting
in some kind of vigil.
They're combining their powers
to make the ki change direction.
To accomplish that
they must control
the five point star
that's centered
on the Chuzenji lake bed.
If we manage to
destroy their strategy
and put a stop to
their evil plan,
what will happen to the ki
that's coming this way?
The ground in Nikko's purified.
If the ki reaches there,
it will be cleansed
and eventually lose
much of its power.
After a while it
will simply go away.
♪
(panting)
Huh?
I can hardly believe
they found us.
Just what should we do now?
Did you hear
what I just said?
Hey, wait!
What is that?
It's Tang shui.
(speaking foreign phrase)
What? Not that!
Ah!
(grunting)
(shouting)
They all disappeared.
What happened to my jinmen?
Don't worry, Saeki.
They became one
with the flames.
That's the way
they wanted it to be.
Reisui, you're insane!
Let's go through!
Mm-hm.
Don't move.
You have to be
trained in feng shui
to be able to attempt it.
I'll try.
The real battle
is about to begin.
Don't, Jinpu.
If I don't come back,
promise me you'll
take care of everything.
Huh--Jinpu, here?
(zapping)
(grunting)
♪
Over here!
Watch the head!
♪
It wasn't easy hauling
that monstrosity.
Good work, men.
It's not great,
but at least we did our best.
Yes.
Will it work?
Yes, but I cannot predict
how effective it will be.
If it only gives off some power,
it'll be better than
having nothing there at all.
We'll have to rely
on Jinpu to help us.
Let's go.
The Senate House.
Why should we save those rats?
Even though many
of our officials
have been accused of bribery,
we can't allow
them to be killed.
You're right.
♪
(soft rumbling)
He's here!
Huh?
Jinpu, you need to understand
why I've come back.
My family had to go through
such unbearable pain
when they left for China.
Many died knowing
terrible suffering.
We have both endured
our share of losses, Reisui.
But our families shouldn't
continue to hate each other
for the sins of the past.
I want some revenge.
That won't help any of us.
We must end this
shameful squabble.
We should make amends for the
good of our country at least.
Never!
Die!
(grunts)
(grunting)
(otherworldly sounds)
(rumbling)
You seem edgy.
Those big shots
we're trying to save
are corrupt and despicable.
I know they are.
I've investigated them.
So what?
Why should we waste
all of our energy
trying to help them?
They're nothing but a bunch
of deceitful criminals.
♪
(grunts)
I'm still obligated to them.
They're human beings.
That's all that matters.
My job as a policeman
is to protect and serve
the community.
My personal feelings
can't interfere with my job.
I made a promise
to uphold this creed
and I will honor it.
Hm.
I'll buy that.
I might have a plan
that will help you.
Would you like to hear it?
Well, I'm open to anything.
What is it?
Those officials are scum,
but I suppose Kawaji is
doing the honorable thing.
(grunting)
His power is equal to mine.
One of us will have
to give up his life
to succeed at this game.
I am not letting go.
I have to win.
(screaming)
Don't do it, Jinpu.
You're going to kill us all.
♪
Reisui, do something.
You've got to stop him.
♪
I won't allow you to
interfere with our dreams
to dominate this country.
♪
Do you hear?
(shouting foreign phrase)
♪
Huh?
What's he doing?
♪
Ah!
Don't be stupid, Jinpu.
The power of feng
shui will be lost
and disappear forever!
If the destruction of feng shui
is the will of Heaven and Earth,
then we must accept our fate.
♪
Hey, he's gone.
(grunting)
♪
Oh...
Jinpu, are you all right?
Our fate was determined
the day the wind
and water families fought.
Did we get them, Kenshin?
I'm not really sure,
but you certainly gave them
something to think about.
Huh?
What's that, hm?
Reisui.
♪
The man who is willing
to make the eternal sacrifice
will be the ultimate
winner in this battle.
Water will reign
over this country.
That's what we've always wanted.
Our dream will live.
It just won't work.
(grunting)
♪
Don't do it.
It's coming back!
They must have
rebuilt their jin.
♪
(gasping)
What is that?
I have waited for this day.
My time has come.
I won't die.
My legacy will keep
my memory alive forever.
(grunting)
Our side will win!
Then my family will
become the rulers of Japan!
I shall fulfill that promise!
We could have lived
together like brothers.
We are feng shui.
Now it'll disappear forever.
(screaming)
♪
As head of the water family,
Reisui dedicated
himself to his mission.
His final act will assure
our family victory over wind.
Saeki.
(grunting)
♪
Reisui was determined
to bring honor
back to the water family's name.
He succeeded by
rebuilding the jin
and taking control of the ki.
The ki's coming.
It'll be here very soon.
(rumbling)
♪
Oh no.
We need to stop it.
Ask him.
♪
Let's talk.
What do you want?
Give me the real
gold heralding device.
That's right.
♪
(trembling)
Sir Horobi Hitu
has just arrived.
Please make way
for Sir Yamahuchi.
The police want us to leave.
That's absolutely preposterous.
Whatever for?
Some sort of security problem.
They won't say what it is.
They're being completely
unreasonable if you ask me.
Excuse me, but I must
ask you to leave, sir.
We can't put their
lives in danger.
This is an important meeting.
We can't cancel it unless
we have a specific reason.
Come on, Chief.
Hm?
Let's go.
A gold heralding device?
♪
What in the world is that?
You know it.
That man stinks
more than a skunk.
(growls)
You weasel!
I want it!
(grunts)
♪
Ah, ah!
Watch out, Sano!
♪
(screaming)
The ground.
It's gone.
How the hell did he do that?
It's actually true.
Saeki does have
the gold heralding device.
It's crazy to let
that lunatic keep it.
(evil laughter)
Yes, I have it,
and I'm never
going to let it go,
so don't make any
attempt to retrieve it
or I'll wipe you off
the face of the earth.
With this heralding device,
I won't need Reisui to help
me take over the government.
Saeki found out about
the gold heralding device
from the decree that separated
Buddhism from Shintoism.
Then I bet he must have
stolen it from the Yome Gate.
He probably kept it
hidden from Reisui
so he wouldn't find out.
It cost Reisui his life.
If he'd know about it,
he wouldn't have had
to sacrifice himself.
Saeki planned that all along.
He was holding it in
his hand and watched
as Reisui died a horrible death
that had no meaning whatsoever,
and it was because he wanted
to control this country
without any interference
from the water family.
It's too late to stop the ki
from heading into the city,
but we may be able to prevent it
from causing mass destruction.
It's traveling at a rapid rate,
so we have to act fast.
First, we must destroy
the stone monument.
Then if we get
a hold of that device,
we can change
the direction of the ki.
Let's just hope I'm right.
Kenshin, no.
There's no time to contemplate.
Come on, Sanosuke, let's go!
All right.
(panting)
(ticking)
(explosion)
-Was that a cannon?
-What's going on?
(rumbling)
(explosion)
(shouting)
Well, can't say we
didn't warn 'em, huh?
Get out of the building!
Explosion!
Whoa, hey, you big buffoons!
One of you at
a time, come on now!
(panting)
You have to face reality,
Battousai the Slasher.
Both you and that
feng shui reprobate
are just worthless
has-beens of the past.
I will be a new
light from now on,
the light of
a shining new empire.
(grunting)
(shouting)
Get out!
Quickly!
(panting)
Relax, it's over.
Is there anybody
that hasn't gotten out?
We're the only ones left.
I checked.
Everyone got out safely.
That's good.
The evacuation has
now been completed, sir.
Hm?
It all came off amazingly well.
If those big shots only knew
how much danger they'd been in,
they would have dragged me
through the mud for sure.
Huh?
It's up to us now.
Do or die.
Do you hear that?
Out of the way, coming through!
Did you make sure the area's
been secured in Kanaji?
Yes, it is secured, sir.
Good, we have to get
over there right away
and see if the ki has
caused any further destruction.
We've done
everything we can so far.
Let's just hope that
our jin will hold up
and protect the city from harm.
Heralding device,
shield this stone monument
and don't let it be destroyed.
You are the bastion of my power.
I'll rule all Japan!
(rumbling)
Ah!
(screaming)
A new day will dawn.
The future of Japan
is in my hands,
and nobody can
take it away from me.
Now I'll be able
to manipulate the ki
and change the entire
structure of the government.
The masses will be
forced to follow my will.
I'm in control.
The light of world shines on me!
No matter what he's thinking,
he's only a human being.
Light cannot shine on a man
who is possessed by evil.
Spirits of Heaven and Earth,
please protect us.
♪
Now!
Ah!
♪
Yah!
It's the force of the spiral!
♪
(screaming)
Jinpu,
catch!
♪
I got it.
No, Jinpu!
(grunting)
I'm going to send
the ki to the southeast
so it can dissipate.
Hurry, move out of the way!
♪
(indistinct shouting)
(explosion)
They did it.
No, for now it is
moving this way.
It might hit us!
There's just no
way we can stop it.
Oh!
(rumbling)
(otherworldly howl)
(otherworldly shriek)
It stopped itself.
Somehow it just
fizzled right out.
They must have done it.
Yes, I believe they did.
Uh, Mr. Kawaji?
What is it?
It looks like
Tsunan's disappeared.
♪
I know where he's gone.
I bet he's gone back
to the Senate House.
He does have a nose
for controversy.
♪
The light...
has gone out.
♪
Jinpu, you did
an excellent job, my son.
But I couldn't have
done it without your help.
You gave us the answers
we needed to defeat Saeki.
The man was insane.
It was all I could do
to protect the city
from the evil influences
he would have brought.
♪
This is too powerful
for ordinary humans.
We should throw it down to
the bottom of Musashino Spring.
I will. I give you my promise.
Take care of our country, Jinpu.
Keep it safe and prosperous
for as long as you live.
Yes, sir.
Goodbye, Horita.
♪
(indistinct shouting)
The building will be as
good as new in no time, sir.
♪
You want to know the
real story, Sano?
The old man was once
the commissioner of the shrine.
His full name is
Horita Masamutsu.
Commissioner of the shrine?
That explains it.
Tell me, Tsunan,
how come you didn't mention
anything about this
in your article?
I couldn't.
I know, you made the article
about the corrupted officials
so big there wasn't space.
Papers need a little
scandal to sell.
Besides, Saeki
immediately confessed
to bribing all those men.
I was pretty impressed
with Kawaji's determination.
Well, that's a surprise.
I never thought
you'd say anything nice
about the police department.
Hm?
Hey Yoshi, quit being so lazy.
I need some help
with this laundry,
so you get off your butt.
It's just not fair.
Why me?
'Cause I'm the boss.
All right, all right!
♪
Ready?
Let's go.
♪
Hm?
I'm sorry, Kenshin.
I would have liked
to have known you better.
I must move on.
I know.
We appreciate all
of your help, Jinpu.
Good luck in all your travels.
Well, I couldn't have done
it without you and Sano.
And I do hope that you're never
burdened with another problem.
Kenshin, I'm very glad
to have known you,
and I hope you have a good life.
I'm sure you will.
And you will, too.
Samurai and feng shui experts
may be out of style
in this new age,
but at least we're not lonely.
It's important that
we direct our energies
in a positive direction.
Our goal should be for
the betterment of mankind,
and then our hearts
and our land will mend.
♪
I couldn't have
said it better myself.
Let us always be together,
in life
as well as in spirit.
♪
(theme song)