♪
This is where you'll
fight the next duel,
and considering
who you're fighting
you'll never leave
this room alive.
Spare me the
sales pitch, will ya?
(grunts)
Very impressive.
Now, where's the guy
we're supposed to fight?
Usui.
Where are you?
Here.
♪
Oh, there you are.
Welcome, gentlemen.
♪
Glad you could come.
So, which one of you
wants to die first?
After I've killed you two,
I'll kill Shishio.
Then use all three of
your heads as decorations.
Usui, Shishio is the
leader of the Juupongatana.
Just what
do you mean?
That was the
agreement we had.
When I joined his group,
I told Shishio
I would kill him
if I had the chance.
(growls)
Shishio knows that?
Of course he does,
but he needed a
fighter like me,
so he agreed to it.
He needed my skill.
Eyes of the heart.
Hmm?
(gasps)
Good for you, Ayumi,
you've made a wise decision.
You couldn't
fight your way
out of a wet grain sack
with that little
blade of yours.
(chuckling)
(groaning)
Anji?
So, you're awake.
That medicine that
Kenshin left me
is a lot stronger
than I thought.
You took care of
me after he left?
You're lucky that
Kenshin had this stuff.
I think you would have
died without this.
You've got some friends who
really care about you, Sano.
(chuckling)
My whole body is aching.
But that's okay.
I haven't had a
workout like that
since the last time
I fought Kenshin.
You're some piece
of work, Anji.
Speaking of Kenshin,
where is he?
He and Saito went to fight
the next duel with Usui.
He's one of
Shishio's group
left here to fight
the three of you
while the rest
went to Aoiya.
You mean, he sent the
Juupongatana group to Aoiya?
You can still catch up with
Kenshin if you go right now.
The room at the
end of the hallway.
Right!
Anji, before I go.
I guess I
owe you one,
but don't think
for one second
that means I'm gonna
go easy on you.
So, next time,
we'll have a real battle.
I don't ever want to
have to fight you again.
You're not a challenge,
but if I have to, I will.
Oh yeah, well, I'm gonna
stay in training just in case,
and I guarantee
that next time,
I'll knock you
into next year.
(grunts)
(snickers)
See ya!
He'll never learn.
♪
Hmm, so.
Saito Hajime, and the
small one is Battosai.
You're sweating and
your hearts are racing
so I suppose you already
know about Aoiya.
Anji must have told you.
I knew he'd betray us
sooner or later.
I'm really not interested
in anything you have to say.
I didn't come here
to listen to you talk.
Kenshin!
Sano, hi.
You all right?
Yeah, just fine, thanks.
So, he's the next one
we gotta fight, right?
Yeah.
Anji did betray us.
That's the only way
a fool like you
could have survived
the first duel.
Ah, well, I guess I'll
have to kill you too.
You are history.
It's all right to
fight when you're angry
as long as your anger
is under control.
Otherwise, it'll
cause muscular tension
that inhibits
flexibility and accuracy.
Out of the way.
While you and Sano
are on your way to Aoiya,
I'll be taking
care of this guy.
-Now, go.
-You mustn't.
It's too late to
save anyone in Aoiya.
You've got to stay
here and fight!
Those were
Shishio's orders.
-Go.
-Next time.
Wait, you can't go!
-Come back!
-You're coming along too!
I'm coming,
Kenshin.
Put me down,
you idiot.
I'm Shishio's lover.
My, my, how
incredibly touching.
One man staying
behind to die
so that his friends can
live a few minutes longer.
What a sweet man.
(chuckling)
Wrong, I have no intention
of dying anytime soon,
and I'm not sweet at all.
As for Kenshin, I plan on
fighting him one day myself.
(growls)
So, I'm afraid I'll
just have to kill you.
Let me go, you brute.
Put me down!
I hate Usui.
I want him dead
as much as you do,
but first, I want him to
kill Saito and kill you next.
But there's no way a guy
like Usui can beat Saito.
You're wrong.
He's a stone-cold killer.
You should have
seen what he did at Kobe.
(screaming)
Are you all right, boy?
Hold it right there!
Who are you,
how'd you get in here?
You, the third guy
from the right.
You have a good stance and
you hold your sword well,
so I guess you were
trained in Satsuma, right?
And how did
you know that?
Lucky guess.
We'll attack him together
working as a team.
♪
Take four men and attack
from his left flank
when I give the signal.
The rest of you get ready
for a simultaneous attack
on his right flank.
So, you're going to attack me
from both sides at once, eh?
My, what a dirty trick.
But typical for
government work.
Surrender or die.
(chuckling)
I'm afraid I can't
make the same offer.
I'm going to kill
you and your men
whether you
surrender or not.
(gulps)
Get him!
(men yelling)
♪
(grunting and laughing)
(groaning)
You're an
arrogant man, Captain,
and because of that I'm going
to make you suffer the longest.
Yes, a slow
and painful death.
Thank you, Captain,
it's been a pleasure.
(laughing evilly)
He's like a killing machine.
(breathing heavily)
♪
Kill me?
Mm-hmm.
I suppose you're angry
because I killed 50 of your
fellow policemen in Kobe.
In fact, the Kobe garrison
was quite a disappointment.
You see, I went there
because I needed practice
and they hardly put
up any fight at all.
Ah, I see your anger
is turning to hatred.
Excellent.
Not even you can
hide your feelings
from the eyes of the heart.
You feel the
need for revenge
and that's what
I want you to feel.
That way you'll provide
more of a challenge.
You're a fraud.
Eyes of the heart.
This power you have,
it isn't witchcraft.
It isn't telepathy,
it isn't supernatural
or magical, it's nothing.
You may be able to
know my state of mind,
but you can't
read my thoughts.
What?
Protecting the
safety of Japan
and the lives
of its citizens
was the sworn
duty of every one
of those men you
killed in Kobe.
Just as it is
for all of those
who chose to become members
of the police force.
No one compelled
them to be cops,
and they knew that it
was a dangerous job
that would sooner or later
put them in harms way.
This also applies to the
members of the shinsen group.
There was no doubt
in any of our minds
that some of us would be
killed in the line of duty.
So you're quite mistaken
if you think that my motive
for wanting to kill you
is for the sake of
those men to get revenge.
I'm going to kill you
because you're the
essence of evil
and the world will be a better
place without you in it.
I'm certain there
are a great many
who would agree with
you if they could speak,
but unfortunately,
they're all dead.
♪
And now the time has come
for you to join them.
I'm going to
shower in your blood.
(grunting)
I guess your great
gatotsu sword isn't so great.
♪
What, only three wounds?
Surprising.
You're good, but you look
mystified and I know why.
The gotatsu has
never failed you before.
So, why now?
Want to know?
Yes, yes of course you do,
so I shall tell you.
Like you said,
the eyes of the heart
isn't anything
like witchcraft
or a supernatural
or magical force.
It has its roots
in the end of an era.
On the day that marked the
end of the Tokugawa era,
and the beginning of
the Meiji restoration,
I fought against Shishio
and I lost my eyesight.
No one had any
use for a blind fighter,
so I was taken to the
woods and left to die.
I couldn't see,
had no idea where
they'd taken me,
and was in
excruciating pain.
I knew that I wouldn't
survive much longer.
♪
I couldn't tell
day from night.
I couldn't tell if
I were alive or dead.
At times, my heart
stopped beating, and then--
And then...
♪
There was a sound.
The first sound
I'd been aware of
in what seemed to be
a very long time.
It was the sound
of running water.
The sound of a stream.
That sound made me
realize how thirsty I was.
So, I rose, stumbled through
the woods towards the sound,
and then I realized,
I had heard the water
from more than a mile away.
Even though it
was a tiny stream,
making barely
any sound at all,
I think it was dying and
then coming back to life
that were the origin
of the eyes of the heart.
Which is really
nothing more
than having super
sensitive hearing.
Once you have
this super hearing,
a human is like
a lump of sound.
Their heartbeat teaches
me their state of mind,
and the quality of
the muscle stretch sound
teaches me their
state of readiness
and when they're
about to attack.
That's the secret of
the eyes of the heart,
and that also
explains why
your gatotsu technique
is useless against me.
Ah, your heart's
beating faster.
That must have
made you angry.
(snickers)
I knew all along that
you were a nutcase, Usui,
but I had no idea that
you were quite so stupid.
What?
♪
Thanks for
your humble story.
To show my appreciation,
I'll return the favor
and tell you about
my eyes of the heart.
Your eyes of the heart?
♪
My ability to
understand an opponent
is quite different from
your super sensitive hearing.
It's foundation
is psychological.
Understanding the true
motivation of the enemy.
In other words, insight
into the needs of
another human being.
Ah, and just what does your
heart tell you about me?
It tells me a
great deal about you,
including the real reason
you joined the Juupongatana.
You said it was
to kill Shishio,
but that's not the
real reason, is it?
When you were
giving your speech
about Shishio robbing
you of your eyesight
and then abandoning you,
your face wasn't full of hate,
you were smiling as if
you were telling a joke
that was amusing
only to you.
And then
I understood.
You don't want
to kill Shishio.
In fact, you'd
be scared to try,
because you know that after
your experience in the forest,
when Shishio himself was
betrayed and was badly burned,
he was even closer
to death than you were
and the power he
developed as a result
is much stronger than yours.
So, when you joined
the Juupongatana,
you did so only
on the condition
that you could
attack Shishio
and try to kill
him at anytime.
Now, why would
you insist on that
if you never really
intended to try?
I'll tell you why.
As long as everyone knew about
your agreement with Shishio,
it would appear that Shishio had
to be on guard against you,
which would make it appear
that he was afraid of you,
and if people thought he was
afraid then they would be too.
You live off
other people's fear.
It feeds you,
nourishes you.
It's the only thing that gives
meaning to your miserable life.
So, killing Shishio is the
last thing you'd want to do,
cause he's a lot more useful
to you alive than dead.
♪
I could be wrong on
some of the details,
but generally, I'm
pretty close to the truth.
♪
(snickers)
(both chuckling)
♪
(both laughing loudly)
Go on, laugh all you like!
Let's see if you're still
laughing a few moments from now,
after I've slashed
you to pieces.
Are you ready?
Are you ready
to die, Saito?
♪
Come on.
Enough talk, I want
to get this over with
as quickly as possible.
I've got work
to do, come on!
Bastard!
(growling)
♪
He thinks he can trick me by
using a tortoise shell shield.
But that trick won't work
against the gatotsu.
♪
What the--?
You see, it's no trick.
The tortoise shell
is so perfectly round
that it will deflect the
thrust of any weapon or blade.
It also prevents
you from seeing
where my next thrust
is coming from.
(grunts)
♪
The tortoise shell technique
is actually very old.
The first ones to use it
were ancestors of mine
in Ryukyu hundreds
of years ago,
and I was the one
who rediscovered it.
♪
Your gatotsu
is useless now.
And yet, you
have to use it
even though you know
you can't possibly win,
because you have
no alternative.
(snickering)
I thank you, Saito,
for providing such
delightful entertainment.
(chuckling)
Oh dear, you've
grown impatient.
Very well, what
are you waiting for?
♪
(groans)
We both know how
this is going to end.
But I'll make it last
just as long as I can.
You're the only one who's
ever figured out the way
I've used Shishio and those
fools in the Juupongatana group.
But that's all right,
since you're never going
to be telling anyone.
You've been taking out your
frustration on everyone else
over not being able
to kill Shishio.
I can see that in
your twisted mind,
each of the men you kill
is actually Shishio.
Do you really think
that Shishio doesn't know?
He's not stupid, you know.
He may be deranged,
but he's also a very
good judge of character.
I'm sure he sees
right through you.
What's ironic is
that you thought
you were controlling
him, but in reality,
he's used you like
a puppet to get you
exactly where he
wants you to end up.
I guess you really
are blind, aren't you?
You go to hell!
♪
Now, you fool, you
are the one who's blind,
and at this close range,
your gotatsu is useless.
Ah-ha, your
heart is racing.
You're afraid,
aren't you?
Because you know that
nothing can save you now.
(snickering)
The killing blow will
come from behind my shield.
Slide through your
ribs and into your heart,
but where will
it come from?
Top, bottom,
left, or right?
If you had true
eyes of the heart,
you would know,
but you don't, do you?
Huh?
(groaning)
(screaming)
How did...
you do that, Saito?
There are several kinds
of gatotsu attacks.
Ishiki, the frontal attack
is the first position.
Nishiki from above,
is the second position.
Sanshiki, the mid-air
strike is the third.
The attack I just used,
the zeroshiki position,
is called
the hidden strike
and you're the first one
I've used it against.
I was saving that
honor for Battosai,
but I was forced
to change my mind.
Lucky you,
congratulations.
Now, I won't ever
take my revenge
for what Shishio did.
Poor Usui.
You're so full of hate that
you still don't understand.
You never had a
chance against Shishio.
You were given
a marvelous gift,
the eyes of the heart,
and all you did
was use that gift
to lead a life
filled with
hate and deceit.
I've lived a life of
commitment and dedication
to a goal and
I never gave up.
Pity that what you
dedicated yourself to was
a complete waste of time.
Just because you were
able to defeat me,
doesn't give you
the right to judge me.
I have lived my life
by a simple credo :
Do unto others as
they would do unto you.
It was a difficult life, but
matters of honor often are.
I wonder how long you will
stay loyal to your credo
like I was to mine.
(groans)
How long?
Till I die.
♪
Kenshin Himura was right.
The Juupongatana have come.
Okina's not strong
enough to fight,
which means there's
only seven of us.
So, we're facing
a real tough job,
but we can do it
if we all work together.
All right!
What do you know,
it finally sounds to me
like we're gonna have
a little fun this time.
You call it fun, huh?
Well, I got news for you,
there are 140 of them.
So, the odds are 20
to one in their favor.
You've got it
all wrong, kid.
These guys are here just
to keep you from running away.
The only fighting you gotta do
is against the three of us.
Just myself and two others,
Henya and Iwanbo.
Well, what are
you waiting for?
Come on out!
I can't cut your heads
off if you're in there!
And I want each of your heads
as a gift for Mr. Shishio.
With a gift like
that, he just might,
well, you know, ask me to--
know what I mean.
That nutcase is a member
of the Juupongatana?
I guess so.
What should we do?
Well, seven
against three
is a lot better than
seven against 140.
Accept the challenge.
What other choice have you?
A plan of attack,
that's what we need.
I think we should take the
offensive and attack them first.
Yes, and we'll
coordinate our efforts
based on which opponent
each of you is fighting.
If you've won your fight
and your opponent
is no longer dangerous,
go and help someone
else who's in trouble.
Kaoru, Yoshi, you two take
the guy with the red hair.
Misao, you take the woman with
the scythe, but be careful.
She's dangerous.
Shirojo, you and the others
take on that huge tub of lard.
That stupid looking fellow with
the moronic grin on his face.
Huh?
If we get through
the first stage
of the attack
successfully, we'll regroup
and decide on
our new strategy.
Good luck.
Right!
♪
Let's go everyone!
(shouting)
♪
I thought you
said the room
where we were gonna
fight the next duel
was just down the hall.
I can't go on carrying you
like this forever, you know.
The swordsman that's waiting is
the best in the Juupongatana.
Though he looks like a kid.
She must mean
Sojiro Seta.
♪
Huh?
What'd you stop for,
come on!
That's Hoji's library.
It hasn't been
used for a long time.
It's vacant.
Kenshin, we are
short on time, remember?
Hey!
He's here.
I told you that's
not the right room.
There's no one there.
♪
There is someone there.
It's Aoshi.
♪
Aoshi Shinomori.