♪
(singing in foreign language)
Saito, Saito!
Hey, Saito!
Today's your lucky day!
Battousai the Slasher
has been spotted!
Several of the villagers
say they saw him
at the bottom of the
mountain this morning,
and I've sent a couple of my men
to go there and pick him up now,
and they'll all be here tonight!
(horse neighing)
Mother Machree.
♪
Kenshin, he's always
full of surprises,
clever and unpredictable.
Battousai, his
name is Battousai.
He's the legendary slasher.
♪
Kenshin, who do
you think you are?
Not a bad entrance with
the horse and buggy routine.
So, how are ya?
Are you ready to become
Battousai the Slasher again?
♪
Come the right time, and
you'll find out Saito.
♪
What, set Edo on fire?
Yeah, we interrogated
Cho, the punk you caught
from the Juppongatana.
He talked all right.
And this morning, we
arrested a guy connected
with the Shishio underground.
He was loaded down with
explosives and fuel in his pack.
He confessed of his plan
to set Edo on fire
around midnight tonight,
and burn it to the ground.
That's diabolical!
I think so too, and
believe me when I tell you
the Shishio group is definitely
the most dangerous and cunning,
and they don't make
stupid mistakes.
Shishio uses mostly assassins
and the elements of surprise.
His men never get
caught, and if they do,
they never talk,
unless they're told to.
So, maybe it's a setup.
Maybe Cho leaked Shishio's plan
as some kind of a diversion,
or Shishio would've sent
somebody to kill him
before he had a
chance to squeal.
You're right.
There's got to be some
other kind of secret plan
that even the Juppongatana
aren't aware of.
Whatever it is,
Edo must not burn.
Gentlemen, come on and
stand up for yourselves.
The time is now for
you to stop hiding
and start fighting like men.
Let's unite together,
and show this broken country
who's really in charge.
Time to wage war!
(chanting)
Let's wage war!
Looks like another
plot, Kenshin.
Shishio lives for
deception and revenge.
I'm sure there must be some
hidden meaning behind this ploy,
something we haven't
thought of, I'm sure of it.
But what could it be?
There must be a clue.
Hm?
Saito!
When the Shogun Yoshi
Tokugawa betrayed his allies
he traveled by ship
to Edo from Osaka.
His defection gave rise
to the Imperial Army.
What if Shishio is using
Yoshi Tokugawa's victory
as his own victory?
That would make sense!
That would mean
the ships are here.
Setting Edo on fire is
just step number one.
He's planning to bombard Edo
from the ships in the bay!
You're right.
They're going to make
this place a fiery hell,
and those maniacs will
stop at nothing.
I'm telling you, Shishio
wants to overthrow
the entire government.
His plan is the own this
city from the ground up,
but he'll have to
get by us first.
Let's go and stop him before he
has a chance to get out to sea!
Huh?
And where do you
think you're going?
(grunting)
You're going nowhere without me.
Wha-what do you mean, Sano?
(groaning)
A little dizzy, Kenshin?
I'd say from the look of things
that maybe you could use a hand.
Oh, man.
Well, I'll tell ya,
it looked to me
like it was a very
lucky punch, Sano.
Who asked ya?
You're wasting our time, Saito!
We might as well start running!
You can't run to
Osaka, you idiot.
-We'll take the carriage.
-I get the front seat!
Straight ahead, straight ahead!
Straight ahead!
Straight ahead to Osaka!
We're going all the way!
(screaming)
Damn, I missed him again.
Nice try though.
Saito, just what the hell
do you think you're doing?
Trying to shut you
up so we can talk.
Ha, forget that!
Now then, where the hell was I?
Oh, yeah, we put 5,000 police
officers on alert in Edo,
and now that's more than
10 times Shishio's manpower,
so we should be able to handle
anything he can dish out.
What about the telegram
that I sent him?
I arranged to have the
officers make the delivery.
So, why don't you tell
me what the message was?
Even if the police can
stop Shishio's scumbags,
we'll still need support
in protecting Edo from fire.
I wrote for Misao's help.
The Oni gang have guarded Edo
since the end of
the Tokugawa era.
Now, they must be
prepared to die for it.
(birds chirping)
Hm, interesting.
I see.
Hey, hey there, Omasu!
Can't you see we're
busy out here?
I mean, yes?
Hey, you might know this.
How much would a black
market Gatling gun cost?
(explosions and screaming)
-Misao, no more explosives!
-It's really starting to hurt.
Whoa, sorry about that.
But you ladies should know
we must always be prepared
with gunpowder if necessary.
My obligation as the Oni leader
is to have enough equipment
to defend this city against
Shishio and his army.
Misao, a Gatling gun
would be helpful,
but true strength
comes from within.
Huh?
I actually believe that Kenshin
saw you as some kind of warrior
with a strong mind, and that is
probably what made him make you
his confidant in
the first place.
Don't you see?
You are already more powerful
that any gun could ever be.
That's because true
strength comes from within.
You're right, Kaoru.
Now I know that
Himura believes in me.
I want to thank you.
Because of you I
know my mission.
Hm.
Hey!
Hey, everybody, great news!
Kenshin just sent us a letter!
♪
How do you like that?
It's going to be
impossible for the police
to contain this madness.
A simple fire?
Oh my goodness.
Shishio wants to burn up Edo.
We have to come up with
our own way to help out.
Okay, what is it?
♪
Since I'm the leader,
I'll tell you.
Our mission is for us to
prevent this fire at all costs.
Got that?
Now get the carrier pigeons,
we're gonna spread the word!
Kuro, Shiro, Omasu, Ochika.
All of you change
into uniform,
we've been called to duty!
The new Oni gang
has got to help!
♪
That's right, but we need
to help also, Yoshi.
You're right.
You know, Kaoru, I never
imagined we would end up
working with the Oni gang
considering that at one time
their members were such
a bunch of cut-throats.
Fly, pigeons, fly!
Spread the news,
my feathered friends.
We have to hurry!
(wheels rattling)
Most of our men are in Edo,
so it's impossible to protect
Osaka as well, you know.
This carriage is fast,
but we may not make it
there until midnight.
One false move,
and Shishio beats us.
We can't let that happen.
What should we do, Kenshin?
For one thing,
stop worrying, moron.
Even if we can't find
Shishio right away,
Edo is strong enough
to withstand one or two
of his bombs
in the meantime.
So, why don't you stop your
yapping and just let me
ride up here in peace, ya nut!
Ahhh!
Will you please keep
that sword to yourself?
No, as a matter
of fact, I won't.
Not until you decide to shut up,
and realize what's
really at stake here.
I don't think you
really understand, Sano.
Shishio's plan
isn't simply to drop
a couple of bombs
on top of them.
It's just a part of it.
Remember the black ship incident
in 1852 when Admiral Perry
from America came to
Japan and visited Uraga?
♪
Perry forced the ports to be
open to trade with the West.
Thousands resisted, some rioted,
and many people were killed.
It was the beginning of the
end for the Tokugawa era.
That history is fresh in the
minds of the people of Edo,
even now, thirty years later.
And whenever an unknown
ship enters into our harbor,
the people of Edo prepare
for what they suspect
will be chaos and unrest.
The government doesn't have
the ability to control
the uprising that will occur.
Therefore, a bloody
coup d'état is inevitable,
and Shishio could
possibly get his way,
and rule the land by force.
I understand.
So, what you're saying is
we're going to have to find
a way to get there even faster.
Shishio won't get things
the way he wants this time.
Let's get going!
Faster now!
I've seen faster
horses on a carousel!
♪
With his knowledge
of the Tokugawa era,
I believe someone as
crafty as Shishio will use
one of two tactics
to implement his plan.
He'll create confusion
by striking in the middle
of the night, or in
the middle of a crowd.
You know, Shishio
has a reputation
for doing the unpredictable.
I feel confident that I have
the best chance of predicting
how he will behave in this
situation, I just know it.
I'm sure that he and his gang
have anchored their ship among
the thousands of other boats
in the harbor for camouflage.
♪
Shishio, are you absolutely
positive Humira can't spot
our ship out here tonight?
He's a very clever,
resourceful, and skillful man.
Relax, Sojiro.
Even if he finds us,
there's nothing he can do.
-You have to be trusting.
-Hm.
You look worried, Ayumi.
Well, I'm so very happy that
you let me come along with you
to see the bombing
raid on Edo, Shishio.
I'm really not one to complain,
it's just that this ship--ah.
So, tell me, what was it
that first drew you to me.
-My great looks?
-What?
No, it was what
was inside of me.
Well, it's the same
with this ship, woman.
♪
Wow.
It's a ship inside a ship.
Incredible.
This ship is our trump card.
It's called Rengoku.
What do you think of it?
Oh.
Shishio.
Hoji, what time is it?
♪
Exactly 11:27.
Thirty-two minutes until
Edo becomes a fireball.
(laughing)
That's good.
(clock ticking)
♪
It's almost time,
something's wrong.
Where's the fire?
♪
Just cool it, Henya, it takes
time for the fire to spread.
(panting)
A message, sir.
They have policemen
placed all over the city,
so none of our arsonists
can make a move.
Oh, those stupid bunch of
idiots, I just can't believe it!
Those bastards.
Looks like we're going
to have to improvise,
and start those
fires ourselves.
Usui, Juppongatana's
original assignment
was to execute all the
high-ranking officials.
Now we will be forced to
kill all of the police,
and even some of
the citizens as well.
The fire will be so fierce
that it will totally wipe out
everything in it's
path anyway, Anji.
We're just going to help
it accomplish that goal.
Wait up, I love a bloodbath!
And just what
am I supposed to do?
Sit here like some numbskull?
Well, uh...
we could always eat.
-Good thinking, Tiny.
-Thanks.
I'm really starving.
♪
It's killing time.
Stop right there.
We are the police, and I order
all of you to go home now!
Stand at the ready, men!
(indistinct murmuring)
-Let's go get 'em.
-No way.
Look at all of 'em.
-See ya!
-Yeah.
Hey!
Ahh!
♪
Hi, go on ahead and run
if you feel like
you're ready to die.
You might look tasty spewing
blood from the top of your neck.
Mmm.
Hey, what's that?
(screaming)
♪
Shishio will not be betrayed.
You will go forward and fight.
If you choose to turn
back you will die!
♪
Charge!
Go get them!
We've got to save Edo!
(yelling)
Let's start the fire here.
The coast is clear, and besides,
the police are occupied fighting
the rest of Shishio's gang.
Right.
(laughing)
Hey, what are you two doing?
-Huh?
Yeesh!
Help, somebody help!
These two are starting a fire!
Huh, where?
Hey, there they are!
(mixed remarks)
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, they've all
got us surrounded.
Looks like we're dead ducks.
Wait, I can explain.
(grunting)
Yes.
♪
Hey, do you guys need
our help down there?
Hey, Misao, thanks, but we
got the whole thing handled.
We don't any help from
your Oni gang tonight.
Right, but all of you
be careful tonight.
We really have to watch each
other's backs, you know.
All right, now all of you
go and position yourselves
to make sure nobody gets
a single fire started.
-Right!
-You got it!
We'll put out any fire we see.
♪
(cheering)
Yeah!
Love and peace!
They're really very happy
to have the Oni gang
right here in Edo.
It's Okina that built
all this good will.
That's right, Yoshi, you
don't know how true that is.
It has taken Okina many
years to get to the level
that he's at right now.
I know, Okina's
such a good fighter
he wasn't even scared
of battling Aoshi.
I'm just hoping that
he'll recover completely.
These guys really
love the Oni gang!
Yeah!
Okay!
Spread out everyone.
♪
Good luck, my friends.
Now let's hit it.
Huh?
Oh.
We were wondering why
my fire hadn't spread,
and now I understand
it's because of you.
-Misao!
-Hey there, look out!
(gasping)
(grunting)
♪
What the hell?
Oh!
Damn it, damn it, damn it.
They're late.
We should be able to see the
city covered in flames by now.
Did you think in your wildest
dreams they'd stay on schedule
fighting 5,000 policemen?
But it's ruining our plan.
Hoji, when did you
become such a worrywart?
It's not ruining anything,
so why don't you just relax?
Hey, you don't seem to be
concerned in the least.
Is something the
matter with you?
Maybe all Shishio needs is
a very invigorating massage,
or maybe it's just
that you're getting
sentimental about
Edo's destiny.
So, is that what
you're worried about?
There's absolutely no reason
for me to be sentimental.
My entire plan celebrates
only the future.
When Edo burns, it will be
the beginning of my reign,
and a declaration of war.
My only regret is not
seeing Battousai Himura's
pain with my own eyes.
-Sir, I see something.
-Great, is it the fire?
No, sir, it's a carriage
on the waterfront,
moving very fast.
What?
(water flowing)
There are too many ships,
Kenshin, this is confusing!
Which one is it?
That's easy, it's
that wooden one.
See the steam coming from it?
It's ready to set sail.
Yes, you're right.
♪
Hell, you gotta be kidding.
That floating piece of
junk couldn't bomb Edo
or manage to damage any
other place for that matter.
I kinda expected a military
ship, but this hunk of tin
I could handle myself.
Oh, no!
How in the world did they
ever discover where we are?
I thought you said our plan
was foolproof Shishio.
It certainly is, and you
had better remember that.
Kenshin has just
read my mind again.
You gotta tell me what
we should do, Shishio.
Are just gonna wait
here for them to attack?
Of course we're
not going to wait,
my little idiotic apprentice.
We must move quickly and prepare
the ship for a departure
that is extremely conspicuous.
Hoji, get everyone inside.
Yes, sir.
Kenshin may have read my mind,
but not well enough.
What do you think, Kenshin?
♪
Let's dive.
We'll surprise them by attacking
the ship from underneath.
-They won't be expecting that.
-Kenshin, look.
I've got just the thing, these
grenades that Katsu gave me.
They'll work perfect.
See, these things have no fuse,
so when we go under water,
we won't need to
carry any matches
to get these grenades
to explode the ship.
Half-wit.
-Huh?
Hey, what is it with
you riding me, Saito?
You're always busting my chops!
Too bad.
Sano, we can't use your grenades
if the detonating device
inside them gets wet.
You should've thought of that.
In water, those grenades
will never explode.
(grunting)
Hey, maybe you got
another brilliant idea
like waiting for them to ashore,
and then politely
asking them to give up.
Let's face it, you're about
as sharp as a bowling ball.
-Hey!
-Calm down, Sano!
-I swear I'll kill him!
-Easy, easy, easy, easy.
What's that?
Huh?
(explosion)
What the hell happened?
Shishio's ship is sinking.
What, did his cannon discharge?
No.
♪
(gasping)
What in Buddha's
name is that thing?
Another ship.
♪
Shishio.
How do you like it?
It's a Meiji black ship, and
it's your newest nightmare.
Rengoku will destroy you all.
♪
(laughing)
(singing in foreign language)
♪