♪
(laughing)
Men, this is our moment!
(cheering)
♪
I've gotta get back
and help Raijuta.
(cheering)
(shouting)
(gunshots firing)
(yelling)
♪
(laughing)
I've gotta help Raijuta.
Please don't let
anything happen to him.
I'm coming, Sensei.
♪
(yelling)
Fire at will!
(gunshots)
(yelling)
(groaning)
This is awful.
Where's Yutaro?
(shouting)
♪
(gunshots)
Hold your fire!
There's too many rifles,
we don't stand a chance.
I think that maybe you're right.
There's no way we could
take on all of them.
What are you saying?
You knew in order to
build a new kingdom,
many of us would have to die.
We either fight for what we
believe in, or die cowards.
I'm sorry.
It is better to die with honor.
-I won't let them stop us!
-Move in!
(shouting)
Fire!
Hey, get down!
(grunting)
(gunshots firing)
(groaning)
♪
Hold your fire!
(murmuring)
♪
Stop the killing!
Stop the bloodshed!
Stop killing each other!
I won't allow this to continue!
Kenshin!
Who the hell are you?
I will fight against
Raijuta myself.
You will wait for the outcome.
Till then there's
to be a ceasefire.
Commander!
♪
What is it, chief?
You should do as Kenshin says,
and allow him to fight
Raijuta all alone.
Kenshin?
Is that who I think it is?
Men!
Hold your fire!
Soldiers and samurai,
we ask for a truce.
Safety your guns,
and sheathe your swords.
Kenshin!
Come on, you guys,
let's follow him.
Mhm.
Sensei Raijuta!
I'm coming to help you,
Sensei, I'm coming!
Sensei?
Huh?
(groaning)
Help, I've been shot.
Can you get someone to help me?
Uh, wait.
I'll help you.
I'm in pain, I need a doctor.
Hey, you're that guy.
The one that tried to kidnap me.
Wait a minute.
I was hired to kidnap you,
I'm sorry I did that,
but Raijuta made us do it,
he ordered us to kidnap you.
-My sensei?
-That's right.
He set up the
whole thing himself.
He wanted it to look
like he saved you
so you'd be indebted to him.
-You're lying!
-It's the truth.
All the others
were deceived too.
All the others were killed.
I was the only one
to escape alive.
(shouting)
(panting)
Uh, Sensei.
I'm glad you found me.
I've been looking for you.
Don't worry, Sensei,
I didn't believe his lies.
Don't you know that I
think of you as my father?
(gasping)
-Kenshin!
-Yutaro!
Yutaro, come here.
So, you're still
alive, Battousai.
That's right, Raijuta.
I've come to settle
a score with you.
You and I will fight together
to put an end to
all of this killing.
What?
We are here battling this
army to have our own kingdom.
This doesn't concern you.
-It's all right.
-But Raijuta!
I will fight him.
Kenshin!
They call you Battousai,
but you look like
a scrawny little kid to me.
I will demonstrate
to you, little boy
what a real master
swordsman fights like.
Watch and learn.
You're about to die.
The Izuna technique.
(yelling)
(explosions)
-Run away!
-We better move!
(panting)
-Kenshin!
-Where is he?
(tree branches breaking)
Kenshin!
(whimpering)
Not bad, little boy.
Next time you
won't be so lucky.
Battousai, prepare to die.
(gasping)
(water flowing)
You're dead!
Please, don't do this!
Hm?
What is he doing?
Please, Raijuta.
Kenshin once saved
me from drowning.
Get away from him.
He is a very brave
swordsman, just like you.
Sensei, I know that you want
to create your own kingdom,
but if you could only talk to
him, I know he'd like you.
-Beat it, kid.
-I won't go.
Please, Raijuta, won't
you listen to me?
Yutaro, get away from there!
Don't you realize by now what
kind of jerk that guy is?
He's not!
I don't want either one
of them to get hurt.
(grunting)
(screaming)
(gasping)
(yelling)
No!
Yutaro's hurt!
That bastard!
Is he alive?
(gasping)
Sensei--
He didn't mean to.
(grunting)
You!
How could you be so heartless?
Sensei.
This young boy looked up
to you just like a father.
You were his teacher, and
this is how you treat him?
You used him just so you
could build your kingdom.
You don't care a
thing about him.
Please tell them.
Tell them it's not
true what she's saying.
So, you think that
she's lying to you?
(laughing)
Well, she's not, she's
telling the truth!
I don't really give
a damn about you.
I just used you so I could use
your house, and your money.
As a matter of fact, I have
no reason to keep you alive.
(whimpering)
You're lower than dirt.
Yutaro would do
anything for you,
and this is the
way you treat him?
You're nothing but a snake.
I've met a lot of scumbags in
my time when I was a slasher,
but you're the worst one.
Kenshin.
♪
You turned many
samurai into killers.
You toyed with
the heart of a boy
who looked up to
you like a father.
♪
Shame on you.
You will pay for
everything you've done.
Hm?
♪
(groaning and gasping)
Kori, please take Yutaro
to Hannah's place.
Have Megumi treat his wound.
-All right.
-Sano, please go with her.
Huh?
There's still a battle going on.
I want you to go with
them so they're safe.
Please, Sano, go with them and
make sure they're all right.
All right, let's go.
-I know the way to Hannah's.
-Okay.
-Yoshi, go with them.
-No, I want to see you beat him!
Let me stay here
and see it for Yutaro!
Kenshin, whatever you do,
please make him suffer.
Don't worry, he's going down.
Pretty cocky, aren't you?
You didn't wound Yutaro
in vain, Raijuta.
I was able to see
your technique,
and you know what,
I'll beat you!
Oh yeah?
That bloodless cut you
inflicted on Yutaro
using the air to create a
vacuum wave with your sword,
we call that the weasel slash.
Hm?
And the reason for that is
only weasels like you use it!
Oh yeah?
Well, you're nothing
but a puny boy,
and you don't stand
a chance against me.
The great Battousai,
what a joke!
I'll carve you
into little pieces,
and feed you to the pigeons.
You will be one more dead body
to add to my list of conquests.
Ahh, get yourself ready to die!
(explosion)
♪
(gasping)
-Did he get him?
-I'm not really sure.
♪
How do you like the
Izuna sword technique?
♪
Huh?
It doesn't matter how
many times you do it.
Huh?
Your technique comes
through the ground.
Your Izuna makes it easy
to calculate its movement,
and get out of the way.
You're not as dumb as you look!
I'll use a flying Izuna.
Eat this!
(grunting)
♪
What is that?
I've never seen anything
like that before.
That's worse than the other one!
(shouting)
♪
(gasping)
(laughing)
See that?
I can cut you!
You're not so
indestructible after all!
Happy now?
What's that?
Does this little
scratch make you happy?
-This wound is pathetic.
-You squirt!
I'm better than you!
This will be the only wound
you'll inflict on me.
-You're nothing but a maniac!
-Oh yeah?
(grunting)
♪
-Impossible!
-Kenshin!
Whoa, Dragon Flash!
(yelling)
♪
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
Dragon hammer flash!
(shouting)
I can't!
Kenshin, you did it!
He was a monster.
That's the end of our dream.
With Raijuta dead, I
guess that we'll never
be able to have our kingdom.
(grunting)
♪
You can die at any time.
It takes true courage to live.
Just what does he mean?
You are a talented samurai.
Use your abilities
to help people.
(crying)
♪
So Yoshi, is it true?
Did Kenshin win the battle?
Yes, Kenshin beat Raijuta!
The killing's over,
no one else has to die!
Unbelievable.
He beat that big
enormous monster Raijuta.
This Kenshin, I
suppose he really is
a living legend after all.
♪
He's only wounded
on his right arm.
He should recover.
However, there is one thing.
What's that?
The nerves and muscles
are severed on his arm.
Unfortunately, there's really
nothing I can do about it.
He'll have some difficulty
using his right arm,
and I'm afraid that, well,
he'll never be able to hold
a sword in his hand again.
Oh no.
This is so unfair, the one
thing he loved in this world
was Kendo and now he can't
even practice it anymore.
Ugh, this really stinks!
Raijuta!
I hope you rot in hell!
(birds chirping)
Hey, Kori, is there
any news about Yutaro?
I heard he didn't
go out of his room
for a month after the incident.
Well, who can blame him?
He can't practice
a sword anymore,
and he treated Raijuta
like a father.
What a horrible thing to happen.
He can't trust anyone anymore,
it must seem like his
whole life is ruined.
Kori, I feel so helpless!
Isn't there anything
we can do to help him?
in our training?
I'm afraid there isn't.
I really wish there was
something we could do for him.
Megumi.
Everyone's so sad, it
feels like a funeral.
We're sad Megumi because we
were talking about Yutaro.
Then this should cheer you up,
we just got a
letter from Yutaro.
Huh?
What?
"Dear friends at
the Kamiya Dojo,
how is everyone?
I'm writing to thank
you for all you've done,
and let you know
that I'm moving."
-Huh?
-What's that?
"I'm moving to Germany
where my uncle lives."
Huh, he's moving where?
"I think it should be
more peaceful there.
I wanna forget
all the bad things
that have happened
to me in Japan.
I don't think that
I will ever return."
Yutaro.
♪
The young master's uncle knows
a very good doctor in Germany.
He believes that this
doctor could be a big help
and heal Yutaro's arm.
I certainly hope so.
That's great.
Yutaro, just as soon as that
doctor fixes your arm up,
you'll have to come
back here and visit us.
We at the Kamiya Dojo will
always welcome you, okay?
♪
Yutaro?
I suppose we should
be getting along,
the ship will be leaving soon.
Thank you very much
for seeing us off.
It means a lot to
the young master,
and thank you all for
everything you've done.
Please take care.
We must be going.
So long, Yutaro!
Please write us, and let
us know how you're doing.
♪
Hey, Yutaro!
Hey, think fast!
(grunting)
Yoshi!
Loser!
You think you could
sneak out of the country,
and forget our fight?
What--why you!
We had a deal, and I expect you
to keep your end of the bargain!
Unless of course if you're
afraid to fight me, is that it?
Do you think that just
because you got your arm hurt
that you don't have to
keep your word any longer?
Well, that's not the
way it works here!
Oh?
Now, either you get well,
and come back here and fight,
or you're a loser.
(grunting)
Oh, yeah?
I will get well, and
come back and fight you!
If I have to I'll fight
you with my left arm.
And you know something?
With my left arm
I could take you.
I'm not afraid of
you or anything else!
-Then prove it!
-I will!
I'll be back here
to trounce you good!
That I'd like to see!
Come back here if
you're not too chicken!
♪
Oh, well.
Looks like everything's
back to normal.
♪
So, Yutaro sailed
halfway around the world
to Germany to live
with his uncle.
Hey!
Don't you forget!
You and I have to
settle the score!
Didn't think I'd let you
off that easy, did ya?
(boat engine whirring)
(birds chirping)
So long, Yoshi!
I will beat you, my friend,
when I come back here.
♪
That day, another name was
added to the list of names
at our Kamiya Dojo.
♪
He was one student
I'll never forget.
♪
Yutaro Tsukayama.