♪
Good morning!
(cranking)
Ugh.
As Confucius once said,
cleanliness is next
to godliness.
Or something like that.
(breaking)
Oh!
(splash)
♪
(squawking)
He slipped a disc in his back?
Yep, Kori and Yoshi
decided to go to the clinic
to help Dr. Gensai
manage to get his work done.
Wait a second,
was there a reason
why you didn't volunteer
to go along, Kenshin?
I mean, what do
those two really know
about medicine, anyway?
Who knows.
They're actually
helping out Ms. Megumi
'cause she will be
in charge today.
Well, I wish him
a lot of luck, anyway.
(crying)
There's no need to cry,
there's a nice lady doctor
here to help your earache, son.
But I was here first!
I know that, ma'am.
Now that I've set the bone,
it's up to you to rest this leg,
at least for a few weeks.
Thank you.
So, Kori, how's it going over there?
(gasps)
I've done it!
Just take a look!
I've come up with
a mystic cure
for any severe head cold!
I wonder what she'd do
for something serious.
I think this patient
is all done.
Who's the next lucky patient?
Ms. Takin!
♪
Pretend earthquake!
Children!
(grimacing)
This mixture I've made
should really help them.
I would suggest drinking
this on an empty stomach,
once early in the morning,
and once again at night.
Thank you Ms. Megumi,
I will give you
my only chicken as payment
for your services.
That's much too generous,
I couldn't take your chicken.
But, if you have
some eggs to spare
that'd be great!
And, I'll bring you
a little bok choy!
Doctor, you,
it's an emergency,
please help us!
What happened?
Some guys from Himeji
we were gambling with
started losing a lot
and they thought
Ryu was cheating them at dice.
So, they decided
to take it out on him
with a couple of knives!
Cut with the story,
if you don't treat
this guy now, Megumi,
then he's gonna die!
We'll do all that we can.
Kori, start making
bandages right away!
Right!
Yoshi, get the antiseptic
and start cleaning his wounds.
I'm gonna die!
You just relax.
Kori, I need you
to loosen his clothing.
He's got three deep
stab wounds, Megumi!
Then we've got to get started.
But she's a woman, Sano,
how good a doctor can she be?
This guy's in a lot worse shape
than I thought,
we've got to stop his bleeding.
All right,
you three hold him still.
♪
This should help.
The other lamp's running out.
Thanks, Kori.
♪
Finally, we're finished.
Now, all we can do is wait.
♪
She did a great job.
(background chatter)
Welcome to Lenny's!
Hello! Table for one?
For a woman doctor,
she sure did a stellar job
of patching up Ryu!
Without even flinching,
she sewed him up
just like he was a kimono!
And she's so beautiful,
I wouldn't mind her treating me!
Help, I think I need a doctor!
(munching)
You two still owe
for your lunch last week.
More rice, please.
Oh?
You must have a tapeworm, Sano.
(laughing)
So I'm hungry!
♪
(background chatter)
Is the medicine going
to taste bitter, doctor?
The bad news is
it doesn't taste good,
but it will help
you breathe better.
After she swallows
that, how long before
we'll see an improvement?
With a lung congestion
like Kaede has,
it might take two weeks
before we see any results.
Be patient.
To speed her recovery,
you could open the windows
for some fresh air.
If it's a matter of more money,
I can pay whatever's necessary.
I want her to have
the best remedy.
Give us the most
expensive medicine!
We want what's best
for our daughter.
I'm giving her the same medicine
Dr. Gensai prescribed
originally.
It's not expensive,
but it does the job.
They just don't
understand, Yoshi.
They really think that
money can buy everything,
including one's good health.
You can't buy
a long life, either.
You mean Kaede's not gonna live?
Sure, she'll live,
as long as she takes
her medicine like I told her to.
She'll recover,
that along with
plenty of bed rest will work.
Believe it or not,
the bedrest is just
as important as
taking her medicine.
(footsteps)
Ugh!
What's the matter?
It's my stomach!
(wincing)
It hurts!
I need help!
Somebody run and get a doctor!
Everybody relax,
there's a doctor right here!
We've got our own local doctor,
it's Megumi!
You mean the lady doctor
from the clinic?
I hear she does a good
job of healing people!
If you're really a doctor,
please help!
You're fine.
There's nothing wrong with him.
Huh?
But I feel terrible!
Where you goin', lady doctor?
Can't you see that guy
needs your help?
Didn't you take
some kind of oath
to become a doctor?
(crowd murmuring in agreement)
The guy's obviously in pain,
and you're walking away?
Yeah, you a doctor or a quack?
So why is she
refusing to help him?
I don't know.
If it's a matter of money,
I'll pay for him!
If he was really sick,
then I would help him.
Now, excuse me.
Megumi, just where
are you going?
Does someone need my help?
I'm a shaman,
and I can cure
almost any sickness!
(clank)
Yojimbo is my name.
It has taken me many days
to come here from
a mystical mountain far away.
There, I was trained in medicine
by artisan fairies.
I am a conjurer,
and my healing spells
work wonders always!
This guy sounds great!
Help, please cure me!
I will.
Hee-yah!
Let there be light!
Ee-ka-ka!
(chanting gibberish)
Ugh!
And now...
(chanting gibberish)
♪
Oh!
Huh?
Ah-ha!
Yee!
Now you must drink this.
It contains enough healing power
to move mountains!
(gulping)
Hey! I can't believe it!
The pain's gone completely!
Oh!
It's a real miracle!
Wow, did you see that?
He didn't even touch him!
He's some kind
of a miracle faith healer
that can cure almost
any disease!
Mr. Yojimbo,
I have a sick aunt at home,
would you please help?
My husband needs to be treated!
Did you see that?
Please help me!
Mmm, I see.
Well, what do you think?
Is it really possible
for someone to be cured
of a sickness
by a mountain witch doctor?
Who knows.
I saw it,
what he did
was just amazing!
And it sure made Megumi
look pretty inconsiderate.
I couldn't believe it,
she just left that
sick guy lying there.
I think you're
misjudging Megumi,
she must have seen something
that no one else there saw.
What did she see?
I have no idea,
I haven't talked
to her about it.
What?
♪
(crowd laughing)
Our little show
really went very well.
And our bigger plan
to discredit
that lady doctor
is coming off
without a hitch.
Soon, no one will go to her.
And after word spreads
about your demonstration today,
all of her patients
will be coming to us,
right, Dr. Yojimbo?
Ahh!
You are correct!
When the townspeople
hear how she left
the man in pain
and how I handled things,
we will rule this town!
And since the people
think I can cure them,
they will pay
whatever we ask!
With as many sick people
as there are in that town,
we will be rich!
All of us!
Uh-huh.
Nobody asked you,
now get us some more sake
and don't waste any money on it,
just steal it!
Yes sir, right away.
After we create suspicions
about the lady doctor,
discrediting the other
doctors in town
will be very easy.
You don't think
we'll be cured here?
Well, she cured me last time,
but I've heard of
a new healer in town
that's performing miracles.
Well, maybe we should go
see that one, instead.
Huh?
♪
Oh, if it isn't
that lady doctor.
She is the one
who wouldn't help!
I thought doctors had hearts!
I'll put your mouth
where the sun doesn't shine!
She's the one that's been
pretending to be a doctor,
and she's not even trained!
♪
This is insane!
Just what is going on here?
(crowd chatter)
-That dish is for table five.
-Mm-hmm.
So what I've heard
is that this Yojimbo guy
will see only patients
that have lots of money.
All the people that go
to him have to pay 1,000 yen
just to see him.
And I understand he
charges a lot more for
the special water
he chants over.
All I know is,
the guys that
are trying to discredit Megumi,
all belong to
the Hishimanji group.
Hishimanji?
Yeah, that's the wild gang
that actually shot a cannon
into the gambling hall in Edo.
They're worse
than the Yakuza,
because they'll do anything
to take over.
Sano, you're not eating.
What is it?
I've gotta go.
A friend is in trouble,
and I've got a strong feeling
that this person could
probably use my help.
Well...
♪
What is it?
Huh?
(hooves clomping)
♪
She's ready to go!
And just where are
you going with Kaede?
She's too sick to be moved,
she needs bedrest!
You know, I think the whole town
thinks a big fake like you
really needs a rest,
so why don't you bug off,
got it?
Hey now, wait!
She can't be--
I told you to get going!
Ugh!
Hey, that's enough!
Ahh!
(smack)
Oof.
You can't do this.
You're wrong!
(laughter)
So you are the doctor
without a heart
I've heard about.
You cannot stop me
from healing this child,
so take your sick ways with you!
Now, you get away from here!
No way, I won't!
Yeah you--
Oof!
Why are you taking Kaede away?
Don't you realize by doing this,
you're risking her life?
Oh!
Oof!
Wait!
I've just got to stop them!
No!
Don't worry!
I'll find out where they go!
(chanting gibberish)
♪
Yeah-ha!
And now--
You stop that right now!
(panting)
How dare you burst in
in the middle of my chant?
Mr. Yoshinoya,
you don't understand.
You can't buy Kaede's health,
she needs her medicine
to get better.
Please leave us alone.
Hold it!
Why should we listen to you?
You saw that sick man,
and instead of helping
you just walked away!
That man I walked away from
was just pretending to be sick.
Yojimbo and his cronies
are fooling everyone.
(grunting)
She's just lying to you!
You!
Ugh!
Just keep your mouth shut, kid,
and you won't get hurt.
Folks!
You're the guy!
The guy that pretended to be sick!
You know what the Hishimanji
do to guys with a loose tongue?
We cut it off!
(laughs)
Then this is a scam!
Get over there
with the rest of 'em!
Wait!
You can't just keep
us all here forever!
(laughs)
Oh yeah?
(smack)
(gasps)
I've been looking
for you, Hishimaji.
You were picking on my friend.
It's time for you
to get picked on.
All right!
You got it, boy!
So let's do it!
Ahh!
♪
Ugh!
(thud)
♪
(smack)
Ahh!
Run and get Kaede!
(smack)
Kaede!
Don't even try it,
you big fake!
You're a big loser!
(laughs)
(smack)
(whack)
Whoa!
(yelling)
(thud)
Oof!
Doctor, please help me.
This should help, Kaede.
I want to thank you very much.
Please accept our
sincerest apology.
I accept your apology,
but it's important
that you both
understand something
about the healing process.
To cure a sickness,
there are several
factors involved.
The patient must follow
the doctor's advice,
take their medicine,
and in the case of Kaede,
she also needs your help.
You both must give her
your love and support.
Oh no it's a--
Get down!
(explosion)
(laughs)
So you think you're
courageous enough
to try to take on
the Hishimanji?
Huh?
(laughs)
One more time!
Looks like they brought
in heavy artillery!
They're probably
gonna blow us apart!
Fire!
(boom)
(crash)
Hey, I'm still inside!
You're wrecking my house!
Ugh!
(laughs)
If you want to live,
you'd better get out
of that house right now!
You certainly have a way
of treating your friends.
Some say sickness
can be the result
of a sick mind,
so I've come to see
that my friends are all right,
and to see if you're capable
of being cured.
Kenshin!
So, are you and
your gang willing
to leave town peacefully?
Well, I'd like to answer
your question in a way
you're sure to understand,
so here's my explosive answer!
Hah!
Fire!
(zoom)
Kenshin!
(slice)
Yeah!
Best thing about
a reverse edge sword
is it cuts everything
but people very well.
Quiet!
Go ahead, kill him!
(crowd yelling)
♪
(zoom)
Ugh!
Ahh!
You Hishimanji
can't match Kenshin!
(clink)
Whaa-ha-hah!
I feel so stressed,
I need help,
I feel like my
colon's gonna burst!
Whah!
Well then, it's time
to let the chanting begin,
Shaman Breath!
But that won't do me any good,
that stuff was just fake!
A-ha, finally the truth!
You're no healer!
You're a fake!
He's right!
Well, I could help.
After all, stress-related
colon trouble can lead
to insanity!
But, if you confess
to the townspeople,
I'll help.
Uh, what happened here?
Dr. Yojimbo's house
has been destroyed!
It's nothing, really,
he just wanted
a little remodeling.
Hey, look everyone,
I got a confession here
signed by Yojimbo,
saying he's a fake doctor!
You better come by
the clinic later.
(gasping)
Why don't you let
those lowlifes alone?
Stop that talk.
Being a doctor
requires me to treat--
Oh!
Sano, are you jealous?
Nah, it's just that
if you treat everyone
that tangles with me,
you won't have time
for those that really need it.
♪
Yojimbo fully recovered
from his ailment
after you treated him.
So, what kind of medicine
did you give him
to take, anyway?
(giggling)
I probably shouldn't admit this,
and don't tell anyone,
but I gave him just plain water!
Can you say placebo?
So now that your back's better,
how does it feel
to be working again,
Dr. Gensai?
Well, it's nice
to be busy again,
but everyone asks,
"Where's the lady doctor,"
when I come out!
They really say that?
I wish people were as interested
in joining a dojo,
as Megumi's patients
are interested in her.
If you were as smart
and pretty as Megumi,
more people would be
interested in you!
What did you say!
-Oh boy.
-Yoshi, ugh!
Those two.
They're like oil and water!
I think this lady doctor's
the best in town!
But there is something
that as a good a doctor
as she is,
even she can't cure.
And Sano's got it!
Next, please!
I can cure anyone that's sick
unless they're lovesick.
♪