♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪
So you really think
you've escaped my wrath?
♪
Ahhh!
Oh, Kenshin!
♪
Just missed his vital organs.
You may have been great
in the Tokugawa era,
but that was almost
ten years ago.
The Shinsen Group
provided me the opportunity
to hone my sword skills
and, as you can see,
those skills are quite sharp.
But I'm just warming up.
Now let's go.
I know that style, it's Gatotsu!
♪
You're dead meat!
You might wanna just ignore
your friend's feeble attempts
to identify my attacking style
because there is no name
for the style I use.
If I were you I'd say your
best chance is to give up.
How can it be that I
believe what he's saying?
This has got to stop.
♪
Get up!
Stop it!
Move away.
♪
He's still very dangerous.
I've got to finish him right now
while he's still hurting
from the stab wound.
Every time I attack him
his reaction time is
getting quicker and quicker.
With every swing of his sword
he regains some of his power.
He's getting closer to becoming
the legendary
slasher I remember.
That's enough.
Huh?
Ah!
Good thing I'm fast.
Never seen that move before.
The loss of blood should
be getting to him by now.
I know his mind is strong,
but surely he can't
expect his body to fight
after such a beating.
(breathing heavily)
♪
Finally, a fighter
worthy of fighting.
Now to settle the matter
of which of us is the best.
You are really in
trouble, Battosai.
This fight's to the death.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop
it, stop it, stop it, stop him!
♪
Argh!
(crash)
Yeah, that's the way to
show him who's boss, buddy!
Kaoru was right.
He's using Gatotsu style.
A technique designed
to kill an opponent
with only one crushing blow.
It's a powerful strategy,
but if you use the same
attacking technique
four times in a
row like he just did,
you can definitely
count on your opponent
to have a counterattack move
to stop you by the fourth time.
Stand up.
I'm sure you want this settled
after waiting so
long to fight me.
There's only one result
I can allow to happen here.
And that's to kill you.
You can try,
I just may kill you first.
♪
Kaoru.
I'm just so scared.
It's like his fight to
the death with Jine-e.
♪
Please don't let Kenshin die.
Ah!
(swords clash)
♪
If Kenshin fights with perfect
technique he will survive this.
But what if he doesn't?
♪
Ah!
Oh.
Huh.
♪
I broke your sword.
Now you die.
I can't stand this,
somebody stop them.
I don't think that's possible.
Sanosuke.
Are you okay, buddy?
I'll be fine,
but I'm not sure
about these two.
Kenshin isn't fighting
here at our dojo.
His mind has transported him
completely back
to another reality.
He's revisiting his
slasher days in Ito.
He can't even hear us.
The only way to reach
him is to find someone
who shared that
turbulent time with him.
Someone who survived with him.
Otherwise we've lost him.
♪
Kawaji.
Yes, what is it, Sir?
How long has it been
since Saito went into the dojo?
He's been there
approximately four hours, Sir.
I honestly think the
fate of our country
depends on those two men.
So do whatever it
takes to hurry us along.
Yes, Sir.
♪
Just look.
Even with a broken
sword he's ready.
He won't quit.
He's from the Shinsen Group.
Unless you quit there's only
one way to end this fight.
Running away from the enemy
is not the way of the samurai,
and we Shinsen live by that law.
(growling)
With bare hands?
He's keeping his sword
for the next attack.
He's an honorable warrior,
but there's only
one way to stop this.
It's over.
Saito has no weapon left but his
fists against Kenshin's sword.
Huh?
No!
♪
Kenshin.
Kenshin's lost his sword
and any advantage he had.
He hasn't got a chance.
Now it's all over.
He's choking him.
Break out of it
before it's too late.
(choking)
He's got Kenshin's
feet off the ground.
He can't use the ground
to get any leverage to help him.
(struggling)
This is it.
The battle that ended
the Tokugawa era.
(panting)
They're both completely
spent physically.
The first one of them
to have the strength
to pull it
together will triumph.
The next blow will
be the last one.
All right.
Time to finish this thing.
Let's go.
Kenshin.
♪
Stop it!
Saito, I order you
to stop fighting.
You were assigned to come here
to measure Battosai's
fighting abilities,
not to try to kill him.
So I got a little carried away.
Just because you're the
Metropolitan Police director
doesn't mean you can stop us.
The police director?
Measure his fighting abilities?
What's going on here.
Saito, you have completed
your assignment honorably.
I know as a member
of the Shinsen Group
you have a lot of pride
in finishing your work.
But I would consider it a waste
to see Mr. Himura
die needlessly.
Please.
I get it.
So you're the one behind this.
Let me guess.
You're a former
Satsuma Clan Royalist,
but now you've become
the Home Minister
of the new Meiji government.
You are Toshimichi Okubo.
♪
Who is Toshimichi Okubo?
Well, if you were to ask me
I'd say that guy looks
like somebody trying to do
a cheap Abraham
Lincoln imitation.
Now there's a brilliant
observation, Yoshi boy.
What?
Three people rendered
remarkable service
and sacrifice in restoring
the Meiji government.
Only one of those
statesmen is still alive.
That's him, Toshimichi Okubo.
So are you trying to tell me
that guy's important?
He's the Home Minister
of our entire country.
That means that he
is the very top guy
in our nation's government.
I'm sorry Saito got a
little rough with you,
but we really needed to
be sure of your skills.
Now please listen to
what we have to say
with an open mind.
Please be honest.
Will you hear us out, Himura?
Of course.
I'm willing to listen to you.
What is a big shot
like Okubo doing here?
To hell with Battosai,
I better report
this to Mr. Shibumi.
I'm sure he'd find
this development
very interesting indeed.
Hm.
Well, since our fight
has been interrupted
I guess we'll just have
to wait until next time
to finish this match.
Your life has been spared.
I'd say the same to you.
Hold it, Saito.
I suppose you want my evaluation
of Kenshin Himura.
Well, I'd say he's
not worth a damn.
But Battosai Himura
is good enough
for the task you have in mind.
I'm done.
I don't understand Saito.
He's certainly an excellent spy,
but I just don't know
what's behind that face.
He never shows any emotion.
Mr. Himura.
I have a carriage
waiting for you outside.
Please, won't you join me?
I'd like for us to talk.
But anything we need to discuss
we can talk about right here.
I'm not the only one who was
responsible for what happened
during that blood bath!
Ah...
I'm not the only one responsible
for what happened
during that blood bath.
What blood bath?
Whatever you have to say, Sir,
you can talk freely
in front of my friends.
You're back, Kenshin, oh, boy!
Oh!
Megumi, he needs help.
Yoshi, hurry.
Go and get my medicine bag
and some bandages right away.
Gotcha.
Oh, Kenshin.
Is he the right man, Sir?
He might be our only candidate.
Now we just have
to make him realize
this mission's importance.
Our time is short so I'll
be perfectly honest with you
about this matter.
It seems that Shishio
has become active again.
So just who is this Shishio guy?
Some two bit troublemaker?
Hey, this really
doesn't concern you.
Makoto Shishio was a slasher
at the end of the
Tokugawa era just like I was.
After I became well known
by the public as a slasher
Shishio took over the role of
the slasher in the shadows.
He was a Nagasu sect Royalist
who never achieved notoriety.
But he was reputed to have
tremendous slashing abilities.
Are you saying he was
as good as you were?
Oh, come on.
I have never even
heard of this guy.
That's because he kept
a very low profile.
Shishio was always secretive
in the way he worked.
Even during that time
almost no one knew he existed.
I never actually met him,
but I was told he
died ten years ago
at the Battle of Boshin.
But I've always
felt the real truth
was he was assassinated
by a fellow slasher
that was probably hired by you.
♪
As a government official
I'm sure you understand.
I cannot go on record as
confirming your suspicions,
but the fact is, you are right.
Our government's aim was to
maintain national security.
By eliminating the slasher
in the shadows discreetly,
we accomplished that.
Makoto Shishio was a
very talented swordsman.
And he fancied himself
a social climber as well.
While maintaining his
secret role as an assassin
he developed contacts with high
ranking government officials
and gained our
confidence and favor.
Eventually the
assassinations he carried out
were so important that if
the government's involvement
ever became public knowledge
the Meiji government would risk
being overthrown.
He made it known that
if he did not receive
a large amount of cash and
a position in the government
he would go public
with his revelations.
Let me guess.
You created a monster and
then you decided to destroy it.
Shishio had become
completely unmanageable.
He was such a high risk
there was no other alternative
but to have him killed.
So we poured gasoline on him
and tried to burn him alive.
But our fiendish
scheme didn't work.
Shishio was severely burned,
but somehow he survived.
He recovered from this
near death experienced
and it deepened his resolve
to cause trouble
for our government.
Shishio surrounded
himself with the frustrated,
the war hungry and
greedy weapons dealers.
He's the leader of this
ragtag underground army
who all share his wish
to overthrow our government.
Every day more people
become committed
to his twisted way of thinking.
We sent in our army
to destroy them.
But they were routed
by Shishio's forces.
So rather than risk
another embarrassing defeat
we've decided there's
only one way to stop him.
And we think the way
to stop him is you, Himura.
I ask you, will you go to Ito
and save us by
finally eliminating
this sick scoundrel?
Well, what do you say?
Are you asking Kenshin
to assassinate Shishio?
I mean, why should he?
He'd be risking his life
even trying to do it.
♪
Your country needs you.
You also would receive
a lot of money as reward,
and we would absolve
you from any guilt
in activities you've
been involved in
that might be
construed as illegal.
For instance, your friend Megumi
could serve jail time
for manufacturing opium.
Don't even think about using me
to convince Kenshin to kill.
He's not responsible for me
and I can face the
consequences myself.
I would rather be executed
than go along with
your blackmail crap.
You guys are pathetic.
This whole mess is
something you created
and now you want
Kenshin to bail you out.
Kenshin's not the man for this.
He's no longer a slasher
that lives for the kill,
now he'd rather share
the quiet life we lead.
Find yourself another guy.
We don't wish to
hear your opinion,
he could save our country,
just shut your mouth.
I see, the only
viewpoint that's valid here
is your corrupt
government's viewpoint.
That sounds right.
This isn't some afternoon tea
we're inviting him to.
This battle could be
for all the marbles.
Speaking of marbles,
I'd say you lost yours.
If our government fails
there will be no peace.
You wanna see no peace?
You two sure have a calm
way of discussing things.
I don't know much about
your Meiji government,
but I have figured
out one thing.
If the situation was
just a little different
you might be hiring
us to kill Kenshin.
Sir Okubo, I understand
by what you've said
how important it is for you
to have Battosai
the slasher for this,
but he no longer exists.
Kenshin will not kill
no matter what the cause.
We will not allow
Kenshin to go to Ito
and risk being killed for you.
No way.
You can't expect that of him.
It's just not fair to
expect him to fix your mess.
And if need be we will protect
him from you with our lives.
What?
Hey, we need a decision
from him on this right away.
Be quiet.
Huh?
What, Sir?
I understand that this
decision cannot be rushed.
We're willing to give
you some more time.
We just hope that you'll
make the right decision
for all of us involved in this.
Toshimichi Okubo?
Yeah, couldn't believe it.
So what are you
gonna do about it?
I got it.
So Saito's working
for Okubo, huh?
What we'll do is
give Saito more money
and have him eliminate Okubo.
And in the process I can become
the next Home Minister myself.
You've lost it.
What are you saying?
We're not talking about
some local official here.
We're talking about the most
powerful man in all of Japan.
You're out of your mind
for thinking we can
get away with it,
and even though it would
please me to see Okubo dead,
you can count me out
for good, you hear?
You're right, Akamatsu.
We can count you out for good.
I guess I'll see
you in hell, you jerk.
Ah!
♪
So, Shibumi.
You think all it would take
is to give me more money?
You Royalists think that you
built this Meiji government
all by yourselves,
but it was us, the
shogunate people,
who laid the foundation
for you money grubbers.
Without our blood you
wouldn't have had a chance
to restore order to our country.
And that's the reason I'm a spy,
to keep people like you from
exploiting the government
for their own gain.
That's what the Shinsen
patrol is all about.
Maintaining order.
Shibumi.
Your corruption could
destroy our government
and for that you must pay.
No.
You are a conspirator
against our government
and the people.
Wait a minute.
Let's talk this over.
I must have something
that you want.
You control a dog with a leash.
People can be
controlled with money.
But you can do nothing
to control the wolf of justice.
Ah!
The Shinsen Group is
still the Shinsen Group.
A wolf is still a wolf.
Nothing has changed.
And no matter what,
a slasher will
always be a slasher.
It's true, Battosai.
♪
I know this is a
hard decision to make,
but unfortunately we
really don't have much time
so then we'll need to have
your answer in one week.
So see you May 14th.
Ah, Mr. Okubo,
I promise you I will consider
what you want me to do,
I just have a lot of
things to think about.
I hope you'll consider
that our country's future
as a peaceful nation
may be contingent on
your decision to help us.
I've worked long and hard.
But if we don't rid
ourselves of Shishio,
everything we've
planned could collapse.
♪
That night was the last time
we ever saw Home
Minister Okubo alive.
There was no way of knowing
that the day he had set
for Kenshin to
give him an answer
would become a fateful
day for all of us.
That was the day it happened.
May 14th was a day that
would ring in infamy
and change all of
our lives forever.
♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪