♪
(singing in foreign language)
One-hundred and forty years ago,
during the turbulent period
at the end of the Tokugawa era,
a samurai named
Battousai the Slasher
lived in Kyoto.
♪
Battousai was the
most powerful swordsman
who slashed people
in a scene of carnage
that cleared the way
to a new era,
the Meiji era.
♪
But as the disturbances ended,
he disappeared.
♪
While his whereabouts
remained a mystery,
the name Battousai
the Slasher
became a legend.
♪
(wind blowing)
Wait!
Wait.
Battousai the Slasher.
Who?
I have finally found you.
You're a gentle-looking man,
Battousai the Slasher.
Huh?
(yelling)
What in the...
Ah!
Huh?
(groaning)
So are you really
the legendary Slasher?
I've heard stories that you
killed three people at once.
No, I'm a wanderer.
All I am is a
wandering swordsman
with no place to go.
Do you think I can slash
anyone with this sword?
(sword unsheathing)
Hey, what is this?
The edge is reversed.
It's a reversed-edge sword.
Why is the edge reversed?
This sword can't slash people.
(groaning)
And you don't see any
evidence of slashing, right?
(groans)
Actually, it's in
perfect condition.
It seems like it's
practically brand new.
You know it wasn't
me, don't you?
You could still get hurt!
Battousai appears
every night,
testing his sword by
killing innocent people!
If you walk around town
at night carrying a sword,
anybody could make a mistake!
And let me tell you this,
you should know
it's against the law
to carry a sword
in the Meiji era!
(high-pitched whistle blows)
And I'm not kidding about this!
(whimpering)
(whistling continues)
You two are dead meat.
(grunting)
♪
My word, I have
never seen anyone
with this kind
of strength before.
It's Battousai!
♪
(yelling)
How did you...
It's not a good idea
to start a fight
with a wooden sword.
(whistling continues)
It's Battousai!
Don't let him
get away this time!
I am Battousai.
Kamiya Kasshin style.
Battousai the Slasher!
Wait!
Let him go for now.
Kamiya Kasshin style
is our style.
He's slandering
my father's dojo
as he murders people.
(sighs)
Boy, is she a
strong-willed woman.
(whistling continues)
(birds chirping)
Huh?
Ouch!
I almost forgot about Battousai.
I wonder what happened.
Oh!
♪
(birds chirping)
I smell miso soup.
♪
I'm getting tired
of carrying this thing.
Let's just throw it in.
-Okay.
-Hi, kids.
Oh, I wouldn't do
that if I were--ah!
♪
Just what's going on out here?
Oh, good, you're awake!
Your little sisters
are so cute.
We're quickly becoming
the best of friends.
Yeah!
Best friends!
I've been cooking breakfast
and these two have
been my big helpers.
It tastes pretty good,
would you like some?
Want some?
♪
You really made these
rice balls yourself?
I can't believe what you did.
(coughing)
Wha-wha-what's the matter?
It doesn't taste good?
My friend, you cook
better than I do.
(descending whistle)
(gong ringing)
(birds chirping)
(giggling)
He must have
treated you quickly.
I'm happy to see that
the wound has healed nicely.
He certainly doesn't
look like a typical
samurai swordsman, does he?
He's a perfect babysitter
for my grandkids.
(laughing)
(sneezes)
Sorry.
So, are you telling me
these cute little girls
are not Ms. Kori's
sisters after all?
Right, they are
Dr. Gensai's granddaughters.
I've been the physician
in charge of this dojo
for 30 years.
But ever since Kori's
parents passed away,
I've been more like her father.
Okay, that should do it.
Mr. Wanderer, if you like,
you're welcome to stay
at our dojo until you
decide to leave town.
Huh?
You saved my life
and I can tell
you don't have any money.
A generous samurai
would extend to you
the same courtesy.
You don't even know me.
Are you sure?
♪
You must have had
a difficult past
to be wandering around,
but we don't have
to talk about it
unless you want to.
♪
Ms. Kori, are you
the master in this dojo?
Yes, my father
started this school
and invented the
Kamiya Kasshin style.
It's not for hurting people,
it's for helping people.
Kasshin sword,
that's the idea.
I can't believe that killer
is using the Kasshin style name.
Battousai is damaging
my father's ideals.
How could he, it's so wrong!
(door opens)
Kori!
Your Kamiya Kasshin students
are ready for their lesson.
Look, I can't beat
Battousai alone,
but I think we can do it
with all the members
of the Kamiya dojo.
Thanks for coming, everyone.
Tonight we need
to discuss the--
Well, uh, tell you the truth,
we're gonna quit this dojo.
Huh?
Friends are talking
about me behind my back,
saying the Kamiya Kasshin
school breeds murderers.
I have to quit your dojo
'cause my mom doesn't want me
training to be a murderer.
I don't think I can go on.
♪
I feel bad.
We were the last
three students you had.
I'm sorry, I feel awful, Kori.
-I'm really sorry.
♪
I will keep this dojo
alive even if I'm alone.
(fire crackling)
What?
(fire roaring)
Hey, you know what, Kenshin?
I think she's crying in there.
No, no, I have to be strong.
I'll survive.
(gasps)
Ms. Kori, what's
going on in there?
Oh my gosh, Kori!
(bubbles popping)
(gasps)
Wait, don't drown yourself!
Oh my!
♪
(gasps)
(door creaks, slams)
Why don't you think about
what you did overnight?
Okay.
Can I ask you one thing?
What is it?
I was wondering
if you remember
a certain student
in this dojo.
He was left-handed
and had a right thumb
that didn't move.
He's the street murderer.
But...
Are you saying that killer
was a student here?
Don't you understand,
the Kamiya Kasshin style
is the philosophy
of non-violence.
There's no way
one of our students
would kill anybody!
You're talking about Battousai,
a bloodthirsty, evil killer!
I will defend this
dojo's name with my life.
That's the only way to
honor my father's memory
and to keep our dojo alive.
Your father...
he would not want you
to defend anything
if you had to lose your life.
No father would want that.
Your late father's
wish would be...
he'd want you to be
safe and happy.
Hm?
You are just a wanderer,
what do you know about how
he would have felt anyway?
(dog barking)
(whimpering)
Your late father's
wish would be...
he'd want you to
be safe and happy.
Huh?
Ah!
♪
Hello?
I am sorry...
for what I said.
Truly.
♪
I said that I was sorry!
I know that you're awake!
Say something, Mr. Wanderer!
♪
Mr. Wanderer?
Whoa.
♪
(wind blowing)
Why didn't I
at least ask his name?
Wanderer.
Wow, he's amazing
with just his left arm!
You obliterated
that thing, Gohei.
Uh, I mean, uh, Battousai.
Sensei Battousai,
are you testing your
sword again tonight?
Yes, I am, it is time.
-So, are you ready?
-You bet.
Yeah, someone's gonna pay for
this useless thumb I can't use!
(yelling)
(screaming)
-Oh my God, he's bleeding.
-Are you all right?
So who else thinks
they can take me?
(groaning)
Kori, stay back.
(all gasping)
-Sensei!
-Hiruma!
-Hm?
Why did you break the rules?
I told you not to hurt people.
That is the essence
of being a Kamiya sensei.
I don't wanna take
lessons from you anymore.
A sword is made for cutting.
This sword is hungry
to taste some flesh.
Ah!
Just like yours.
(yelling)
(growling)
It's too bad you won't
be able to hold a sword
with that hand anymore, Hiruma.
You...
You are expelled.
And don't ever come back
to this dojo again.
(laughing)
(whimpering)
♪
(laughing diabolically)
(gasps)
(sighs)
I remember.
The guy whose
right thumb got slashed.
♪
It's here.
He was expelled 11 years ago.
Hiruma Gohei.
(door opens)
♪
(laughing)
So it was you after all!
Yeah, you finally remembered me.
For the past 11 years,
I've been waiting for this day
so I could destroy this place
and send the Kamiya
Kasshin style to hell!
Revenge is why you
slandered my father
with your street murders!
♪
Thanks to your father,
I have trained my left hand
for 11 years.
Oh, and I would
love to show him
how good my left-handed
killing skills really are.
(panting)
My father's Kasshin style
will not be defeated by you!
(yelling)
♪
It would be useless.
(gasping)
(grunting)
My revenge will be
complete when I bury you
and destroy this dojo.
I will send you to hell slowly!
First I will make
you kiss my feet.
But what do you think,
should I let you guys
have slashing practice first?
Yes, let me do it.
-Me too.
-And me!
But a sword is supposed
to protect people.
Yeah, right!
(laughing)
Well, cutie, too bad there's
no sword to protect you now.
(grunting)
(yelling, gasping)
What?
What is it, Nishiwaki?
I tried to...
(grunts)
Ah, Wanderer.
You better let her go right now.
Hey, you're that guy
from yesterday!
I guess I should have
taken care of you
when I had the chance.
Wanderer, you're
no match for this guy!
Do you also believe
that the sword
is there to protect people?
No.
♪
I believe a sword is a weapon.
And the real truth is...
kendo is a technique for murder.
♪
You see, Ms. Kori thinks
the I am a harmless man
and that I could
never kill anyone,
even if it was for
the good of others.
How I love her
naive perception of me
and I wish it were the truth,
but I'm afraid that it isn't.
Oh!
So, how many of you
want to get to know
the real me?
(growling)
Go get that little twerp
and torture him right now!
(grunting, muttering)
Run!
Stay back, I don't
want to hurt anyone.
Well, it won't
be us getting hurt.
Just your death.
(yelling)
♪
(grunting)
How'd he do that?
He takes out four to
five people with one swing!
It's magic!
No, he's just quick.
He anticipates your every move.
♪
Red hair and that cross
there on his cheek.
Why, this guy, he's--he's...
I forgot to tell them.
The technique used
by Battousai the Slasher
is neither the
Kamiya Kasshin style
or self-taught.
It's Hiten Mitsurugi style.
It utilizes a killer sword
combined with the speed of God
which slaughters everyone
who stands in its way.
You mean to tell me
you are the real Slasher?
Oh my!
(gasps)
That's very interesting.
We don't need two
of us, now do we?
I'm the only one who deserves
to be called Battousai.
If I kill you, then
I'll be the strongest!
So this is it then.
Die, Battousai!
-Up here.
-Huh?
Ah!
(yelling)
I don't have any affection
for the name "Battousai,"
you know?
But I...I sure wasn't
gonna let that idiot use it.
Of course, he couldn't hold a
sword in his right hand anyway
with that bad thumb of his.
Unbelievable,
this guy's amazing.
He took these guys
out singlehanded
and they're still alive!
Would you please
go get the police
and tell them what
this guy has done?
And could you move it?
Yes, sir, yes, sir!
♪
I'm very sorry,
Ms. Kori, really.
I didn't want
to hide it from you.
It's just...
♪
I guess I didn't want
you to know about it
or want to frighten you.
(sighs)
♪
Farewell.
But...
wait!
-Wait!
-Ah!
You're not just going
to leave, are you?
Wait a second, let's talk.
How can I revive the
Kasshin style all by myself?
Why don't you help me a little?
I told you I don't
care about your past
or what you've done before.
But after the news of this
Battousai imposter spreads,
if I remained here,
then all the effort
we put into restoring
your dojo will be lost.
I never said that I wanted
Battousai to remain here.
I want you, the
Wanderer, to stay here.
Oh!
Well, if you insist on leaving,
you could at least
tell me your name.
Not the name of
some legendary slasher
or any other nickname you have,
just your real name.
Himura.
It's Kenshin Himura.
♪
Kenshin.
Kenshin, I'm sorry you must go.
(door closes)
Oh!
(sighs)
I'm a little tired of traveling.
♪
I feel like staying put
for a little while.
♪
And you said you
liked my cooking.
Well, you're a much
better cook than I am.
I hope I don't accidentally
see you in the bath again!
Well, that's all right
'cause if you ever do...
(groaning)
Oh no, I thought you
were going to avoid it!
That ox sure has
one heck of a kick.
♪
Now, don't move your jaw.
But it hurts!
Baby!
♪
And that's how
Kenshin the Wanderer
joined our Kamiya dojo.
♪
(singing in foreign language)