♪
(theme song)
(grunts)
♪
(groaning)
Yah!
I'm not gripping this right.
Kenshin keeps it
above his shoulders.
Like this.
(groaning)
Ow!
(groaning in pain)
Huh?
Um...
Uh, excuse me?
Um, yeah, that's mine.
(grunts)
The strap's torn.
Huh?
I think I can fix it.
(fabric tears)
♪
There, all done.
It's not perfect...
but it should
be all right.
It's great!
I appreciate it!
I should be on my way.
So, good luck
with your practice.
♪
Oh, what a dummy.
I forgot to tell her thanks.
(gasps)
♪
(grumbling)
Hmm?
♪
What's the matter?
No appetite?
You're miles away.
Uh, huh?
I was just thinking.
What's that?
Stuffed in your waist.
Huh?
Oh, that's nothing.
Oh, really?
Well, maybe your
girlfriend fixed
that up for you?
When did you get a girlfriend?
Who said I have
a girlfriend?
(loudly munching)
I brought everyone
some more tea.
-Hey, Tsubame!
Huh?
(spits)
(groans)
Thank you very much, Tsubame.
Hey, I just remembered
you haven't been around.
You two haven't met yet.
Oh.
(chuckles)
I, uh...
Tsubame's brand new.
She's been here
since last week.
We love Tsubame!
Will you play
a game with us later?
Mm-hmm!
Tsubame, we need
a bucket of water
from the well!
Right.
We're so happy she
came to work for us.
She's extremely responsible
and very polite
to everyone she meets.
Excuse me, I forgot
to tell her something.
I'll be right back.
(groans)
That kid's nuts!
(grunting)
Here.
Oh!
I'll do it.
♪
I meant to tell
you earlier today...
What?
Well, thank you.
♪
I see what's up.
It's puppy love.
(chuckling)
Thank you.
I don't know your name.
What is it?
-Me?
-Mm-hmm.
My name is Yoshi Myojin.
Myojin?
Thanks so much, Yoshi boy.
♪
Huh?
Yoshi...boy?
Oh!
What do I look like?
Some kind of a punk kid?
Hello, Tsubame.
(gasps)
♪
(chuckles)
How's the job
working out?
The word is everybody
in the restaurant
really trusts you.
♪
You come with us.
So, how much is there?
Answer me!
How much money
is in the drawer?
Not very much.
They don't keep
a lot of cash around.
The owner keeps
most of the money
in his pocket,
then he takes it
home each night.
Yeah, that's about
how I figured it.
Let's have the mold
of his house key.
You did get it, didn't you?
I told you to get
a clay impression
so I could make a copy.
Don't hold out on me.
This is wrong!
You're a former
royal guard!
If you commit robbery,
you'll bring shame
on your whole family.
Since when does
someone like you
dare tell me what to do?
(shrieks)
You listen to me,
little girl...
for over 300 years
my family has been
the master of your family.
When I give you
a clear order,
I don't expect you
to talk back.
I was just trying
to protect your name.
Don't worry about me.
I can protect my own name.
Heh.
You just keep
following my orders,
because if you don't,
I'm gonna kill
everyone in the restaurant.
You understand?
Hold it!
Ah?
Where are you?
I'll teach you
to interfere.
The Royalist era
has been over
for 10 years,
and you're still
trying to force this girl
to be your servant?
It's a despicable act,
and I refuse
to allow it.
Now, you have to answer to me.
Who in the hell are you?
It's my friend, Yoshi boy.
Oh!
Can you just forget
about that "boy" part?
Oh.
(grunts)
(groans)
(grunting)
Yoshi boy?
No more "boy" okay?
I'm sorry.
Just forget about
involving this girl
in your dirty plan,
otherwise you're gonna
have to take me on,
and I'm a descendant
of samurai.
All right, boys.
Take this samurai out.
(grunts)
♪
You stupid brat!
All right!
I can see my technique
is good enough
to take these guys.
Practicing each day has
improved my skill level.
I hate to say it,
but I have Kori
to thank for that.
♪
Yah!
(groaning)
All right, let's
finish him, guys.
No, no, leave him alone!
(grunting)
Take that!
You little shrimp!
I'm gonna help him.
Just hold it.
Why are you stopping me?
He's outnumbered.
It's not even a fair fight.
Are you just gonna
watch him get
slaughtered out there?
He will never get
any better if we
bail him out every
time he needs help.
Besides, he'd be humiliated.
We've gotta wait.
He has to prove
to himself
that he can do
this on his own.
(grunting)
Mikio, stop them!
Please, stop!
This is for knocking me down.
You little shrimp!
That'll teach him.
Come on!
He doesn't have
anything to do with this.
He was only
trying to protect me.
Here, I'll give
you the mold, okay?
Hold off.
That'll be enough for now.
Right.
And don't ever
challenge me again.
See you around, Yoshi boy.
(laughing)
Yoshi boy!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I could've beat them
if it was one-on-one.
I apologize.
This is my fault.
It wasn't your fight.
I'm so sorry
if you were hurt.
(cries)
What's their plan?
Huh?
They're coming
tomorrow night.
All right.
I'll be there.
Yoshi boy--oh!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
If I'm not able
to beat these punks,
I still am a boy.
And don't feel bad,
none of this
is your fault.
You didn't get me
involved in this fight,
I jumped in on my own.
Don't worry, though,
I'll get myself out.
And you too.
♪
I can't go to the police.
If I turn these guys in,
they'll arrest Tsubame
as an accomplice.
I can't go to Kenshin
just because I'm gonna
fight with a gang of punks.
Looks like I'm on my own.
This is my battle.
♪
(grunting)
(boards rattling)
How will I ever
be able to beat
that many opponents?
Ahem.
Huh?
Hey, Kenshin.
Hi.
♪
Do you mind
if I sit down?
Huh?
Oh, no.
♪
I've been trying to
practice on some areas
where I don't have
much experience.
Could you tell me
something, Kenshin?
Hmm?
How can a single person win
when he's facing
more than one opponent?
Is this something
from real life
or are you making
it up to test yourself?
I'm just trying
to cover all my bases.
I see.
I've got something
that might help.
Really?
It's from the samurais.
They were completely
outnumbered at the end
of the Tokugawa era and
they had to do something
to even the odds.
The secret is being
able to run fast.
You run away?
Yes, but not to escape,
only to outdistance
your enemies.
Of course,
they'll come after you,
but since everybody
runs at a different speed,
they'll catch up
with you one at a time.
The faster guy
catches up first,
you turn, slash him,
and run away again.
You repeat this with
each of your opponents.
I get it.
I have to warn you,
you've gotta have
strong legs to pull off
a strategy this complicated.
It's exhausting.
I see what you mean.
It's really
a brilliant technique.
You wanna make sure
no matter how many
opponents you have,
you control the
pace and fight them
one at a time.
It's a slick strategy.
Smart.
♪
Hmm?
Oh yeah.
One more thing.
If you start
this strategy,
you have to finish it.
There's more at risk
than your own life.
This approach is used
to protect people,
and the bottom line is
there's no margin for failure.
It's all or nothing.
Oh.
If you lose the battle,
you're not the only
one who suffers.
The person you're
trying to protect
also loses their life.
Oh.
Wait, aren't you
going to the store?
You're headed the wrong way.
I'll go later,
I'm taking Suzy home
to put her to bed.
Huh?
♪
Mm-hmm.
The life of the person
I'm trying to protect
depends on my
skill as a warrior.
There is no margin for error.
Defeat is fatal.
I commit myself to the
success of my mission.
I cannot and will not fail.
(shuffling)
(chuckles)
Let's go, boys.
Huh?
Hey!
Ha-ha!
Why, you little brat.
We should've killed you!
You're right,
because if you
want these keys,
you'll have to catch me.
Get that kid!
Go!
Yeah, let's get him!
Come on,
we'll catch him.
(steps approaching)
Tsubame?
Huh?
Kori.
I knew that you'd
come down and try
to stop this robbery.
(chuckles)
(panting)
We'll get him!
Come back here,
you little kid!
Come here!
(panting)
You're trapped, kid.
Yeah, give us
the keys now.
This is perfect.
Yah!
If you want them,
you'll have to take
them from me.
Your choice,
it doesn't matter to us.
Fine!
♪
Hey, what are you
fools waiting for?
An engraved invitation?
Go take him out!
♪
I get it.
This kid's strategy is
to pretend to be trapped
so he can take on all
my guys one at a time
then turn around
and knock 'em out.
He's got much more
smarts than I gave
him credit for.
Everybody kill!
Take him down!
(laughs)
Uh-oh.
♪
(grunts)
Huh?
♪
Oh, I know that guy.
He's supposed to be
a cold-blooded killer.
The other one's
just as dangerous.
♪
(shouting in fear)
Forget it, Mikio,
I'm out of here.
(grumbling)
You cowards!
He's just a little kid!
Huh?
(chuckles)
I knew you wouldn't let him
face the whole gang alone.
Just observing.
Here I am,
a master of the Kogen
Itto-ryu sword technique,
and the only one
I can use it on
is a bratty little kid
in a dead-end alleyway.
Oh well.
Since that's
the only choice...
♪
This'll be his first time
fighting a swordsman one-to-one.
I'm not worried.
I believe he has the
talent to handle it.
Just watch.
♪
Are you ready to die?
Try me!
♪
(groaning)
(grunting)
You're just
much too slow.
There's no place
left for you to run.
(heavy breathing)
(chuckling)
(shouts)
So, what kind of
death do you prefer?
Decapitation or
a thrust to the heart?
There's no way out.
This is it.
Yoshi!
Don't give up.
You have to keep fighting.
Please don't stop now.
If you lose the battle,
you're not the only one
who suffers.
The person you're protecting
also loses their life.
I can't let him win.
If I do,
he'll kill Tsubame
and then go after my friends.
Do it.
♪
Yah!
(groaning)
(shouting)
(gasps)
(grunts)
(panting)
'Atta boy, you pulled it off!
You gave him
the old one-two.
That was brilliant!
You just proved why you're
my number one student.
Would you mind
explaining why
you happen to be here?
(imitating animal noises)
There are no birds
like that in Japan, guys!
(chuckles)
Great, now you sound
like a dodo bird.
Let go of me,
Mr. "I've got a plan."
♪
I, well, I don't--
It's all right.
You don't need
to thank me.
Watching you
defeat Mikio like that
was a real inspiration to me.
Huh?
I won't be scared
if anyone tries
to bully me.
From now on,
I'll be brave.
♪
I'm glad!
You could give her a kiss.
I mean, after all,
you've earned it.
Hey, butt out!
Oh boy,
he's embarrassed.
Be sure and keep up
your sword training.
I bet you'll be
famous one day.
Hmph, you better believe it.
Someday I'm gonna
be just like Kenshin.
Well, you couldn't
have a better model.
Good luck, Yoshi boy!
Could you please drop
that "boy" business?
Oh!
Hey now, there's
a name to remember.
(laughing)
Just forget it!
Sounds cute to me, Yoshi boy.
That name's not cute!
Don't ever call me that!
I don't wanna
ever be called
"Yoshi boy" again!
♪
(theme song)