♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪
What do you mean?
You've gotta be lying
about Han'nya being dead.
I swear I'm telling the truth.
Four members of the
Oni Gang were killed.
They were all trying
to protect Aoshi
when they were machine
gunned to death.
I can see Beshimi
dying in a fight,
but no one could kill Han'nya.
I was there,
they were great fighters,
but even they couldn't
outrun a gatling gun.
They all died.
What a waste of four men
with such abilities.
As a samurai son I give
you my word it's true.
Because of that
terrible massacre
Aoshi now wants to
avenge your friend's death
by killing Kenshin Himura.
He thinks killing Kenshin
will prove to everyone
how powerful the Oni Gang is,
even though Kenshin had
nothing to do with their demise.
I can't believe
Aoshi would do that.
And that so many of my
dear friends are gone.
♪
You are the first outsider
that's ever been
allowed to visit us here,
and we welcome you, Aoshi.
Now tell us what has
prompted your visit.
I wanted to talk
with you, Shishio.
To get some information.
But let me make
it perfectly clear,
I'm not here to join
your little group.
I see.
Well, I'm disappointed,
but I'll help if I can.
You're obviously skilled enough
to be part of my organization,
but as much as I admire you
I sense you like
to be your own boss,
and I'm the only
boss around here.
Now, is this about Battosai?
Because if it is I do
have information about him
that's very valuable.
Before you tell me anything
I want you to understand
I'm not offering to
kill Battosai for you.
Got it?
Yes, I understand.
Now why don't you stop
jumping to conclusions,
relax and really hear
what I have to say.
I know you want to go
after Battosai alone
and I wish you good luck.
So what is this
important information
that you have about him?
He just acquired a new sword
after a fight with our man, Cho.
I already knew that,
so if that's it I'll be going.
Stop, I have an idea.
There's an old man named Okina
that would know
Battosai's whereabouts.
Now I know he's a former
member of your Oni Gang, Aoshi,
but if we attack Okina,
Battosai will try to help him.
And if he doesn't
help the old man
we'll torture Okina and
he'll tell where Battosai is.
Hm, that just might work.
What's your feeling
about this plan, Aoshi?
Do you think it would work?
♪
Misao, the time has come
for your Aoshi to move on.
You'll stay here
in my safe care.
Mhmm.
Okina has agreed to
take care of Misao.
At least here she
will have a safer life
than traveling with us.
Right, Han'nya?
I know what you say is true,
but that doesn't change
how much I care about Misao.
I wish she could
stay with our gang.
We all want the best for her
and we agree this
situation's it, right?
This is the best thing
we can do to save her.
Our lives are permeated
with death and danger,
and our precious
Misao deserves better.
Don't lie, Han'nya,
even though you know
this will be good for Misao,
you're hurt inside.
I agree with whatever
you say, boss.
Let's get moving
before I change my
mind about that child.
When I eliminate Battosai
then I can finally
claim the title
of the most powerful
one in all Japan.
So what do you think, Aoshi?
Do you mind if we
move against Okina?
I could care less
what you do to Okina.
The only thing I care about
is having Battosai left alone
for me to deal with.
Then you and I are going
to be working together.
Excuse me, great Shishio,
but there is one
matter that concerns me.
Tell me what it is,
I'm your confessor.
I know Aoshi's a
great swordsman,
but if he can give up a
member of his gang that quickly
how much can we trust him?
About as much as
he can trust us.
Aoshi is a shark that could
turn on us at any moment,
but I already knew that.
Of course, I understand.
But for now he serves
a vital purpose for us.
Sojiro, go keep an eye on him.
I'll accompany you.
♪
(shouting)
Just because you
swing your sword
doesn't mean your opponent
will act accordingly.
You're anticipating too many
moves ahead in your mind.
The passage of time has
not been kind to you.
You developed some bad habits
that really need to be broken.
But I don't have much time.
Shishio and his
gang are so ruthless
that he's probably attacking
even as I sit here practicing.
I must hurry.
Please, teach me a
new move before I go.
♪
I see, he appears to
be sheathing his sword,
but in reality he's doing
the double dragon thrust
sword pulling technique.
It's quite a tricky move.
♪
Ha, I didn't over
anticipate that time.
Now he's gonna remove
his sheathe from his belt
and then he's gonna
pull his sword out
and I can charge in.
Wait a second.
Ahhh!
♪
And to think that you
call yourself a master
of the Hiten Mitsurugi
when you don't even
know how to counter
the double step Ikazuchi.
Hey, get up, stand up straight.
You will never master a new move
if a light hit to the gut
keeps you down
this long, Himura.
Come on, get up.
We haven't got much time.
Besides, I only hit you with
the backside of my sword.
(panting)
Huh?
♪
Look at his eyes.
He still has his fierceness.
He won't quit,
he has the heart of a tiger.
He might not be able
to defeat Shishio,
but if I work him
a little harder
it just might make
the difference.
♪
Sensei, I thank
you for your help.
Now I must go and try
and save my friends.
I don't think you're
quite ready for that.
All right, then.
Let me help you master
that last technique.
And if you don't get
it right this time
you'll be paying
me for this lesson
in bruises and lumps.
Now let's start again, move.
♪
Fukuro.
The Fukuro are a secret
ninja attack force.
They specialize
in night attacks.
Attacking the hideout of
a former Oni gang member
is like jumping
into a cobra's den.
But I'm sure the Fukuro will
make very short work of Okina.
♪
I'm trying to sleep, you idiots!
All right, I wanna
know just who sent you.
Ha.
In my day our poison
did a lot better job.
Don't yell for your friends,
we already took care of them.
I gave all of them
a knuckle shampoo.
We heard they worked
for Shishio's gang.
This is Aoshi's doing.
Aoshi must have aligned himself
with that bastard, Shishio.
It's six.
I told those Fukuro
to report back here.
Hm?
I got a message for you.
It's...
Damn.
What the hell happened?
My whole Fukuro force
has been wiped out.
I'm not surprised.
You and Shishio's
lackeys have no idea
of how to do a professional job.
So when their
lives depended on it
your killer force
couldn't take out
an old, decrepit
former Oni gangster
even though he
sleeps like a rock.
I suppose I could retrain you,
but it would take years.
"This is a challenge to that
worthless warrior, Aoshi,
who doesn't have the guts
to do his own bidding.
I'll be waiting for you
at the place at high noon.
Come alone".
So, Aoshi, just how do
you interpret this message?
Will you go?
I understand.
♪
So, Aoshi.
You tarnished the pride
of the Oni Gang once again
with your cowardice
and murdering ways.
You've left me no other
choice but to destroy you.
♪
It's ironic that it
would all come to this.
After the way he helped
me when I needed him
Okina is forcing me to
kill him with my own hands.
♪
Where is he?
I don't know, he left.
So did he tell you
where he was going?
He just put on his
old uniform and left.
Hm.
Hey!
I think he went fishing, Misao.
He looked serious.
If he's wearing his
uniform it's serious.
So I see that he also took
along with him his weapon.
So I guess he's not really
fishing like you said, Kuro.
I'd say he's probably hunting.
Hunting for a fight.
We're sorry, Misao.
He's gone after Aoshi.
Huh?
Did you just say Aoshi?
♪
So you've come Aoshi, well.
I was wondering if on
top of being gutless
that you'd lost your
nerve completely.
You sure lost your honor.
It's about time you
were exterminated
like a filthy rat.
You were a member of the
Oni Gang before I was born.
♪
But now you must die.
Thanks for finally
telling me the truth.
Misao, it's no use,
it's too late to stop them.
I hope the fighting's over
by the time she gets there.
I'm really sorry for her,
she must be feeling
just terrible about this.
She is the loser no
matter who lives or dies.
She's in the middle
between heaven and hell.
♪
If they fight to the death
I'll lose either the man
I'm closest to in my life,
or the one whose
love I want the most.
At this point it's just a matter
of waiting to hear the news.
Well, if you want me
to take care of Okina,
I know Juppongatana well enough
to do the job.
You know that Aoshi is
already on his way, don't you?
Yes, I know.
I've got something
else in mind for you.
What?
Answer this for me, Hoji.
Do you really believe in hell?
No, Shishio, I don't.
Oh, I see.
It doesn't matter
whether you're good or bad.
When we die all we feel is dead.
After we die I don't
think we feel anything.
I disagree.
I believe in hell.
It's real.
Allow me to expound
on my theory.
Let's start with Battosai.
He survived the
bloody Tokugawa era.
He battled Aoshi before.
He knows there's a hell.
How about Okina?
His parents were
killed by Royalists
right before his eyes.
Aoshi has betrayed him.
He knows the pain of hell.
I was burned alive.
Every square inch of my
skin was screaming in pain,
begging to die.
So, Hoji, have I
changed your mind?
Don't you think there's a hell
right here on
earth after all, hm?
Don't you think a world
that's been baptized in blood
should be called hell?
I sense you need
to be persuaded.
And now you shall die!
♪
So it's tonfa.
I think you know deep
in your heart, Aoshi,
that I am the only one that
can beat you one on one.
and I know my steel tonfa
is the answer to your
Kodachi Nitou sword style.
You can't slash
through my defense,
so you had better try
something different.
♪
It's your flowing water attack.
I think this is your
best offensive move.
But you see,
no matter what technique you use
you still have to come
in to get me, right?
And that's when I'll get you.
♪
Crossed Jinyang!
My Kodachi Nitou style
sliced through your tonfa
like it was bok choy.
What gave you the illusion
that you could defeat me, Okina?
I don't care that you
were in the Oni Gang
or about your tonfa,
there's nothing my
twin swords can't stop.
♪
Please don't let
them kill each other.
Okina, Aoshi, be alive.
♪
He's so skillful.
There's no comparison to
the Aoshi I knew years ago.
He's even better now than he was
as head of the Oni Gang.
By forsaking his emotions
and turning into a murderer
he's truly tapped
his inner strength.
He's found a twisted
path to enlightenment.
I'll give you one more chance
to tell me about Battosai.
Where is he?
Tell me where he is, Okina,
and I won't attack you again.
You insult my courage?
I'm just an old solider,
but I'm not like you.
I will not change my principles
to satisfy your needs.
I'll never give in!
♪
I see.
You leave me no other
choice, old friend,
but to kill you and go to town
to ask the others.
You know with those words
you've chosen to die.
♪
I'll give up my
life to defeat you.
I must give my all
to protect Himura
and defend our country from
people like you and Shishio.
♪
No.
Ah!
Please Buddha, don't
let me be too late.
♪
Oh!
Got ya.
Huh?
That stance he's in.
Dammit, it's the
Herculean Sword Dance.
You're both all right.
♪
Okina's life's over.
Wait, Mr. Aoshi.
How, how could you?
Why did you do it?
Go away, Misao.
If you're not really on my side
I never wanna see you again.
Do me a favor and tell Battosai
I'll be waiting for him
at Shishio's hideout.
I see.
But what is it that makes
your hand as hot as fire?
When they tried to
burn me to death
one of the results was
that my body's sweat glands
were completely destroyed.
Since then my body gives
off intense amounts of heat
through my hands and
other parts of my body.
Sometimes it's so hot
I feel like I'm on fire.
♪
This heat has changed
the way my brain works,
it's given me new insights into
our world and our experiences.
I've accessed a deeper truth.
Through this phenomena I've
made some startling discoveries.
The true nature of
man is to murder.
This world is a living hell
and my goal is to
fill it with murderers.
And I will be the leader
of this murderous nation.
If you don't believe in hell
then why the hell should
I keep you around, Hoji?
Why are you visibly shaking?
I hope I haven't scared you.
No, Sir, I,
I am just trembling with joy.
It's rare that a
man is lucky enough
to serve a leader of destiny.
Someone brave enough
to build a new Japan.
I was shaking
because I'm so excited
just standing here with you.
It's great, Ayumi,
to see the conversion of
yet another loyal murderer
to our vision.
He had 35 stab wounds.
Even though Okina survived,
the doctor said he
could die any time.
That's for sure.
He was lucky.
I guess it's kind of a miracle
he lived through it all.
But he's still not
out of the woods yet.
Okina lost a lot of blood.
So how's Misao taking this?
She's fine.
She seems to be holding
it together for a girl.
Don't call her that!
Shut up!
You sure got a lot of nerve.
So who died and made you Buddha?
You sure have a big mouth
for someone with
such a wimpy body.
(shouting)
♪
Misao.
There's something I need
to share with you now.
Okina told me to give this to
you if anything bad happened.
"For Misao.
Ciao, my lovely Misao".
Oh.
Ciao, my lovely Misao.
The fact that you're reading
this means that I've passed on,
but don't shed tears,
don't be sad.
You can still find me
in the summer wind,
you can feel my warmth
in the morning sun.
I will always be with you.
When I decided to fight Aoshi
I knew it would be dangerous.
I'm ready to die the
death of a warrior.
As of now the Oni
Gang no longer exists.
Leave any fighting
or revenge to Kenshin.
Now, my dear, please listen.
You must give up your
dangerous lifestyle.
Learn to exist peacefully
and live a normal life.
How can I do what you ask of me?
♪
Misao, what is it?
The Oni Gang still lives.
And I will not let it die.
No, Sir.
Aoshi is through as
the gang's leader,
and I will be the new
leader of the Oni Gang.
I will stop Shishio
and his followers
by working with Himura
to see them crushed.
I'm planning a special
kind of revenge for Aoshi.
When I get my hands on that
spineless eel he'll be dead.
Oh, yeah.
♪
Okina, how could you
ask me to turn my back
on the only family
I've ever known?
I will rebuild the Oni Gang.
Once again its members will
possess the code of honor
exemplified by Okina,
a man of courage and respect.
There is no happiness
for me without this.
Misao, I hope you'll
take this the right way,
but were you struck in the head
while you were sparring today?
I'm not Misao anymore.
From now on call me boss.
I'm the boss of the Oni Gang.
♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪