♪
(singing in foreign language)
(wind howling)
(grass rustling)
(wind blowing)
Huh, I don't like this.
(gasps)
That's strange.
The daylight is
turning into night.
♪
(wind blowing)
(low rumbling)
(gasping)
(slow footsteps)
Oh, it's you!
You call yourself God's Child.
You've been warning everyone
by threatening and
killing innocent people!
♪
(wind howling)
(shouting)
What is that?
Your cheap magic trick
doesn't scare me,
Child of God.
You think you can
intimidate everyone?
Well, not me.
I don't believe in you.
(footsteps)
I warn you.
Don't come any closer.
♪
I'll show you for what you are!
Let's go, God's Child!
♪
(groaning)
(panicked shouting)
♪
(low rumbling)
(birds chirping)
-Kenshin!
-Huh?
That guy is here.
You know, that guy.
They say that he can turn
daylight into night.
He has magical powers.
(gasps)
(cicadas buzzing)
That was weird.
The sun disappeared.
What could cause a thing
like that to happen?
It was a miracle, Mommy.
Shogo made a miracle.
It was a miracle,
wasn't it, Mama?
You shouldn't say that.
Huh?
Mmm.
(footsteps crunching)
Shogo made a miracle?
Who's Shogo?
(cicadas chirping)
Cho, can you hear me, Cho?
Hey, Cho?
(grunts)
Battousai.
It's good to see you.
Good to see you.
Are you all right?
I think I'll live.
Uh huh.
This man was a complete master
of the Hiten Mitsurugi style.
That's right.
Now there's somebody
else who knows
the Hiten Mitsurugi style,
besides yourself.
But this man is evil.
I've never felt that kind
of terror before today.
He wasn't human, I tell you.
Is he the man they call
Child of God?
Yeah,
but he's not.
I'd say he's more like
the child of the devil.
Hey, Battousai.
He is more skilled
than even you.
Don't fight him,
because if you do have
to go up against this guy,
you will die.
He will surely defeat you.
Stay away from him.
Hey, what are you sayin'?
Kenshin defeated
the fearsome Shishio
in a battle to the death.
He's the greatest.
Yoshi!
This young man fought valiantly.
-He almost died today.
-Uh...
So did anyone
else get hurt?
Yes, as a matter of fact,
another young man, named
Shiraishi, was killed.
He was one of the ones
who received a warning.
Now all of those who
were warned are dead.
Know who they were?
I checked out the background
of the three men
that were warned
and then later murdered.
I found out that they were all
prominent Christian leaders
during the Tokugawa era.
Christian leaders?
Yes, Christianity was banned
during the Tokugawa era.
It was a very dark era.
What do you mean?
What did they do?
During the Tokugawa era,
anyone who even believed
in Christianity at all
was severely punished.
And that included
women and children.
But in spite of that,
followers went underground
and continued to
practice their religion.
Some still hide.
So Kenshin,
are these killings
some kind of a payback?
I don't know.
We still don't know
what the swordsman
Shogo Amakusa's intentions are
or what he is thinking.
My guess is that this
is only the beginning.
(gasps)
Misao.
(whimpering)
Misao, what are you doing?
You have to stay in bed.
Otherwise, you'll get worse.
I can't stay in bed.
We got a note from
one of our agents.
It's about Master Hiko.
He's the one who taught
the Hiten Mitsurugi
style to Shogo.
Master Hiko is still alive.
(gasps)
(waterfall roaring)
(footsteps crunching)
Must be an entrance behind.
(water dripping)
(group chanting)
God is good.
He watches over us.
He protects the weak.
He heals the sick.
All things are glorious
because of him.
He is the source
of my strength.
He makes all things possible.
He watches over us
and the children.
My beautiful brothers and
sisters, may God bless you.
Blessed art thou
who are pure of heart.
May God bless us.
Blessed art thou
who are poor of heart.
May God bless us.
Blessed art thou
who are rich of heart.
-May God bless us.
-What's goin' on?
Who are these guys?
Blessed are you who love God.
God will be with you
to bless you forever.
May God bless us.
♪
(water drips)
(glittering chimes)
I will now bless each
and every one of you.
I will bring you
to God's country.
Don't be afraid.
Follow me and believe.
God's country is for you.
We belong there.
Wow, she's truly noble.
She's a miracle that will
take us to God's country.
(passionate shouting)
Who is she anyway?
And what is she doing?
(waterfall roaring)
I'm gonna find out
who she really is.
Where are they going?
Huh?
(gasps)
Oh!
(cackling)
♪
Wait, Lady Magdalia.
Just don't pay any
attention to them.
Come on, let's go.
♪
(chuckling under breath)
You're blocking my way.
So, you're supposed
to be the big holy mother.
If you're so holy,
we should all be
bowing at your feet,
shouldn't we, your highness?
Huh?
(laughing hysterically)
This is a public walkway.
Even the police
don't have any right
to stop innocent people
from going about
their business.
-Come on, Shozo, let us go.
-All right.
Wait a minute.
It's our duty to find out
if you're innocent
or not.
You see here, toots.
We got a report that there
was a suspicious gathering
going on here.
Aha.
Very nice.
Hey!
Don't stoop to their level.
I guess I'm gonna have
to keep this
for evidence, ha!
Enough!
(punching)
I always thought
that four against two
are really unfair odds.
Don't you?
Yeah, who the hell are you?
Don't interfere with the police.
You've just made a big mistake.
(shouting and groaning)
Why, you little--
(grunting and groaning)
You're the ones
who are interfering.
All right.
It's safe now.
(groans)
(gasps)
What did you go
and do that for?
We didn't ask
for your help.
-Shozo.
-Right.
(gasping and moaning)
A shoulder blade.
Several arms, legs,
and ribs are broken,
but I think they
can still walk.
Let's find something
we can use as a splint.
Right.
Agh, get away!
(Shozo growls)
Shozo, don't do anything.
You won't get
away with this.
I won't rest
until I get you.
You understand?
Come on, you guys.
You gonna lay around all day?
Come on, get up.
Get outta here.
Maybe you can go to
the doughnut shop.
-I'm sure they're open.
-Shut up.
What, why are you
taking their side?
I just saved your life.
No, thank you.
If I had wanted to use
violence as a solution,
then Shozo would
have taken care of it,
but you had to
butt into something
that was none
of your business.
Now we'll have all kinds
of trouble with the police.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I was only trying to help you,
but at least I was able
to get this back for you.
But since you don't
appreciate it, I'll keep it.
No, you can not.
As a matter of fact, I can.
I got this back for you,
but you're not even
gonna thank me for that.
I'm sure some pawn shop
will give me money for it.
So long, heh.
You really think
you're something special,
don't you, lady?
You can't insult
her like that!
(screams)
Now, give that back.
Why is this so
important to you?
You want this
thing so bad?
We'll fight over it.
(gasps)
If you can defeat me,
you can have that
important medallion back.
♪
You ready?
This guy's really good.
He didn't hit me,
but my clothes are torn.
That's not bad, right?
You're the first one I've met
that's been able
to avoid my Fire Dragon.
Ready?
(growls)
Darn it, my bone
still isn't healed.
Eat this, tough guy.
♪
We're not done!
Hey, you!
I said the match
isn't over yet.
It's over.
You're the one that
wanted to fight, not me.
Remember?
Besides, what's to prevent me
from knocking you
right into the river?
You wouldn't hit me
like this, would you?
(tree breaking)
(screaming)
(whip cracking)
(water splashing)
No!
(water surging)
Hey!
Help!
(water bubbling)
(bird tweeting)
(breathing heavily)
Why didn't I just give this
damn thing back to them?
I wonder what that
symbol stands for.
Whatever it is,
it's really important to them.
(grunts)
And she' calls me violent.
(birds chirping)
♪
The man who taught
the Hiten Mitsurugi style
to Shogo Amakusa
is a man by the name
of Hyoei Nishida.
He used to live in China,
but he has since
moved back to Japan.
He lives in
a very secluded area,
and he is quite ill.
I'm afraid he doesn't
have much time left.
You may find your
answers with him.
Good luck, Himura.
♪
Hm?
(cicadas buzzing)
Good afternoon.
I am looking for
Master Hyoei Nishida.
(footsteps)
(gasps)
(pained groans)
You must be Master Nishida.
Yes.
(coughing)
And you must Kenshin Himura.
Yes.
Hiko told me to expect
a visit from you.
As you can, I'm not
long for this world.
I have to tell you everything
I know before
I die, Mr. Himura.
These three murders are only
the beginning, I'm afraid.
There is going to be
more violence very soon.
Eventually, I predict,
there will be a big
war in Shimabara.
In Shimabara?
That's right.
Shogo Amakusa is determined
to start a big war.
He won't stop until
the present government is dead.
The reason for that is
to establish his own kingdom
which he calls God's Country.
God's Country?
(moans)
Are you all right?
I must finish.
Shogo was really a genius.
I took him under my wing.
I was entrusting him with
the future of Christianity,
but at the time he
was still just a boy.
But he, uh, he made
the decision that power
was more important
than peoples' rights.
♪
(thunder crashing)
Listen to me, Shogo.
Don't do it.
That goes against God's wishes.
I don't care.
I swore revenge.
Someday I will
go back to Japan.
I will destroy
everything there.
I will do it for the people who
were slaughtered and mistreated,
and nobody can stop me.
Then I will build God's Country
that I will oversee myself.
Stop it.
What you are proposing
is against the
very will of God.
I don't care!
I don't need God.
(thunder crashing)
What?
Hyoei, you once
told me of a legend
in the Hiten Mitsurugi style,
Kenshin Himura,
the one they call Battousai.
♪
This heroic sword will be
the death of Kenshin Himura,
the death of Battousai.
This sword has
attained the true
Mitsurugi Ryu style,
which surpasses his
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
He can't stop me.
And when he's dead,
I'll be God.
(thunder crashing)
Shogo, I was wrong to trust you
and teach you
the Mitsurugi style.
You're insane,
and you must be stopped.
Mitsurugi will not
be used for evil.
♪
Since that fateful day,
I have been blind, sightless,
unable to ever
see anything again.
Rai Ryu Sen,
the Thunder Dragon thrust,
the technique he used
against me back then.
It was the the first offshoot
technique created by Shogo
after the Hiten Mitsurugi
style had culminated.
He is a genius,
unfortunately
a demented genius.
Mr. Himura...
unless we can
stop this madman,
Shogo Amakusa,
a horrible catastrophe
will occur in Japan.
There is only
one person alive
that has even
the remote chance
of stopping Shogo.
(pained moaning)
Master Hyoei.
Master Hyoei!
Please, Master Hyoei,
don't leave us.
Battousai, you're the only
one that can defeat him.
He's lost all sense of reason
and a lot of good
people will die.
You must stop him.
You're our only
hope now, Kenshin.
For you are,
the great Battousai.
(whimpering)
♪
(sighs)
Master Hyoei?
Master Hyoei!
(woman sobbing)
♪
(woman crying)
Battousai the Slasher.
I will meet you at Shimabara.
♪
Yes, I will meet
you there, Shogo.
♪
(singing in Japanese)