♪
(singing foreign language)
(clacking)
We won't be able
to catch a ship to Osaka
for at least three days.
What are we gonna
do until then?
We'll have to
make do, I guess.
Let's just relax and enjoy
ourselves for a change.
But it's going to cost us
a bundle to stay at the inn,
not to mention feed Yoshi.
Boy, I can't get enough
of this tasty blowfish.
I'm tellin' you,
this is my kind of town.
Hey, you're supposed
to taste your food,
not inhale it.
Yeah, Yoshi, you gobble
it down just like a pig,
it makes me
sick to my stomach.
As a matter of fact,
I think I'm starting
to lose my appetite.
Waitress, another
bottle of sake, please.
Sure thing.
Yoshi, for heaven's sake,
would you at least try
to use your chopsticks?
Quit harping at me,
you both look like
a couple of blowfish.
Ha ha ha, but I bet
they wouldn't taste as good.
You smell like one!
Hey, what did you say?
Listen, you imbecile,
I demand to have
another beer.
I'm not gonna
give you anything.
Cough up some money now,
or I'll throw you
outta this place.
No way, old man.
You've humiliated us
and now you're
going to have to pay.
We happen to be members of
the Democratic Rights Movement.
They call us the Tenguto.
(grumbling)
Give us some respect!
Listen, if you
guys want a brawl,
we'll give you one.
Don't waste time on amateurs.
I always like to
stay in practice,
especially with a bunch of
dummies like you guys are.
Oh, I'm really scared.
No women and children, please.
We wouldn't want
them to get hurt.
(lightning striking)
(groaning)
Yeah!
Ugh.
Not too shabby,
but try this.
(gasping)
Oh, no.
Mm-hmm.
Come on, are you afraid?
(growling)
Wait, do you hear
what I said?
Don't proceed
any further.
Huh?
(footsteps clanking)
Wow, that guy looks like
a big fan of kabuki.
Hey, watch out!
Here comes Battousai!
Huh?
Did he say Battousai?
He'll put a stop to this.
Go, Battousai!
He's the best.
♪
That's right,
I am Battousai the Slasher.
The same man
who made it rain blood
in the streets of Kyoto.
I've become
a legend among men
and they tremble
whenever they hear my name.
So who thinks
he could fight with me?
Huh?
Look here, on my left
arm is a cross mark.
That proves I'm
the true Battousai.
How come you don't have one?
Kenshin, what happened
to your cross mark, huh?
It's on my face.
Misao, have you flipped
your lid or something?
You want a cross mark,
here's a cross mark.
Perhaps we've
been wrong all along.
What do you suppose
we should do now, boss?
Japan has been peaceful
for some time now.
I've been able
to put my legendary
Hiten Mitsurugi sword
into retirement.
But I have no qualms
about using it
and if I'm tempted,
it can result
in a blood bath
like you've
never seen before.
(growl)
Now which one of you
guys is stupid enough
to take on
the wrath of Battousai?
Huh?
Hah!
I'm out of here!
(yelling)
Come back here.
Count on this.
You may still rule the roost
around here, Battousai,
but we'll be coming back.
Huh, they don't seem
very scary to me.
(cheering)
You're number one!
Hey, you bit galoot!
Huh?
Um, no need to thank me.
I was just doing
my job, that's all.
That's not what I wanted
to say to you at all!
I'm a man of peace now,
and my fondest desire
is for everybody
to experience happiness
in their lives.
I do everything in my power
to make that happen.
And hopefully I'll make up
for my sins of the past.
This is pretty weird, guys.
I don't know what
we should do about it.
Maybe we should ignore him.
Well, we better do
something, Kenshin.
Think of it
this way, Kori,
at least he isn't
doing anything bad.
Hey, look!
-Hmm?
I insist, please
take this, Battousai.
I can't possibly take
any of your money, sir.
That just wouldn't be right.
Mm-mmm, Mm-mmm.
What a snake in the grass!
(throat clearing)
Change your mind?
But the man wanted
to give him money, Kori,
what's so wrong with that?
The guy's claiming to be you.
I don't think it's
worth the trouble.
Come on, guys, let's just
forget about the whole thing
and find somewhere to stay.
Oh, well, I'm gonna strip
the sheepskin off of that wolf.
Huh?
I can remember being
in Kyoto when all of a sudden
we heard the
swiping of a sword.
The enemy was
the Shinsen Group.
There must have been
a hundred of them
and they were
bloodthirsty thieves,
but Battousai prevailed
and slew every
last one of 'em.
(laughing)
It seems almost impossible
that one man
could slay a thousand,
but I slashed away
and I was finally
able to beat them
into submission.
Then I pummeled them
until they were all dead!
-Will you?
-Master.
Please, take this.
They're paying him
to protect them.
(door opening)
This place is awful, too.
I don't know where
we're going to stay.
Kori, listen,
the man's actually
collecting a bodyguard fee.
What?
But that could
be called fraud.
That means he's no better
than those awful
hoodlums we met.
Let's put a stop to this now.
It's fine with me.
He's just a common thief.
That's right.
Are you sure?
It's as clear as day.
This place used
to be affiliated
with the Choshu Clan.
That explains
why everyone's
so familiar
with Battousai.
He was a hero to
the townspeople here
and they really worship him.
It would be easy for
someone to make a profit
by borrowing his name.
Yeah, but he didn't
look like such a bad guy,
maybe we ought to
check him out some more.
Anyway, that's
just my opinion.
I don't know,
I beg to differ, Kenshin.
The same here.
We'll check him out.
But let's find an inn,
my arm's feeling
sort of numb.
You must have eaten
a bad blowfish.
It's possible,
he was chowing down
like there was no tomorrow.
Come on, let's go.
To the doctor?
No, to that faker.
Huh, arrgghhh!
(seagulls squawking)
(birdsong)
This temple looks
deserted and empty.
It could have happened
when the law to get rid
of God and Buddha
was forced into effect.
Why that big jerk, look!
Huh?
The sign says, "Battousai's
Hiten Mitsurugi Style Dojo."
Huh!
Well that joker must
have some kinda nerve.
Well, I've had
enough of this!
Hey, fishface!
Come out fighting!
Huh?
Well, well, did you come all
the way out here to thank me?
After all,
that wasn't necessary.
Oh, come on,
why would we do that?
That's pretty funny,
you should work as a clown.
Huh?
♪
Kenshin, why don't you
tell this guy what's going on?
Listen, if you've got
something to tell me,
don't be shy about it.
Well, uh, you see,
it's like this.
Um.
Come on, Kenshin,
just spit it out.
(punching)
(cow mooing)
You must know kendo,
judging by that sword there.
Oh, I get it,
you've come by here
so I could give you
a lesson in my famous school.
Well, I consider it
a pleasure to give you a lesson.
It always makes me glad
to help those
weaker than myself.
Huh?
(rooster crowing)
Hmm, you should
be grateful to me,
Battousai doesn't
always have the time
to take new pupils.
But, uh, well--
Let's start with
your stance, okay?
Stand up straight.
(banging)
That's pathetic, kid.
Hey, come on now,
pick up your sword
and let's get going.
Sorry, Battousai.
Does this look
any better, sir?
The tip is too low now!
That's way too high,
you have to watch your hips
and straighten
your back, will ya!
All right, try to relax
your shoulders a little bit.
You're stiff as a board!
Does this position
look any better?
Yes, but your
concentration is lacking.
You have to keep your focus.
All right, that's it,
I've had about
enough of this crap!
(crying)
Sudisa's being mean to me.
But Shedo pushed me first!
I'm gonna get you for this!
Would you boys please
stop fighting now?
Sensei.
Huh?
Hmm?
I got to go.
Huh!
Come on.
♪
I'm hungry, when are
we gonna get some food?
But you just ate breakfast.
Oh, do me a favor,
could you take this
little girl off my hands?
Sure, I'd be
glad to help you.
Hey, don't cry,
it's gonna be all right.
Now where's the outhouse?
Come here,
you big tattletale!
Hey, now!
For God's sake, what kind
of dojo is this anyway?
(chiming)
Uh, Miss Kori,
make sure you give them
the same amount of rice,
otherwise they
may start fighting.
And don't forget
to blow on it
so they don't
burn themselves.
All right.
Maybe I can solve
your problem.
If you can't find
a place to stay,
you're all
welcome to stay here.
Huh?
In fact, I insist.
(grimacing)
We accept,
thank you for the offer.
Hey, are you nuts?
(hollering)
♪
(cow mooing)
(kids playing)
I did a little investigating.
What'd you find out, Misao?
I found out plenty.
Remember those men we met
at the blowfish place?
They said they were
members of Tenguto.
Yeah, but they
were never members
of the Democratic
Rights Movement.
It was a big fat lie.
They're just a bunch
of common criminals.
Those guys manage to cause
all kinds of
trouble in this town,
it's horrible.
Ever since that fake
Battousai appeared,
they've laid low.
There's been no crime at all.
Well, that must account for
why people like him so much.
Right, but he still
makes money off them
and that's wrong.
But he's not using
the money for himself,
he's using it to look
after those little kids.
The sensei was
telling me about them.
Apparently, these
kids are orphans.
It seems their parents
were put to death
because of political views
and the children
were then abandoned.
Now I understand
why he's doing it.
It's probably the only way
he could think of
to support and take care
of those poor kids.
Yeah, I guess
you're right, Kori.
Maybe they should
give that guy a medal.
(snoring)
(giggling)
Come on!
♪
Damn, we can't let that
Battousai cramp our style.
We've got to
outsmart him somehow.
That's right,
our reputations will
be reduced to pond scum
if we don't do something.
Then why don't
you just kill him?
Huh?
What's the matter with
you guys, are you scared?
Who are you, huh?
♪
Tenguto warriors aren't
afraid of anything.
(glass breaking)
Wha!
Jurobei Anzai has
come here to help us.
He'll take care of Battousai,
we have nothing
to worry about.
Master Anzai has actually
seen him in battle.
He was present
at Mount Ramalama
during the upheaval
and studied his technique.
He is correct.
I will never
forget him.
He was large,
just like you described,
with powerful muscles that
protruded out of his body.
This job will be quite
expensive, my friend.
We're prepared to pay
you what you're worth.
It will give me great
pleasure to kill Battousai,
but pleasure isn't enough.
(crowd talking)
This cabbage is wilted,
couldn't I get a discount?
No one would ever guess that
this whining wimp is Battousai,
not in a million years.
Aw, come down a little,
I'm begging you.
'Cause I have a bunch of kids
at home that need to eat.
(grunting)
That man is a real odd duck.
What's with the kabuki makeup?
I don't know,
but he's very resplendent.
(humming)
Battousai,
come and meet your match!
-Huh?
-Hmm?
We're here to settle the score
between you and the Tenguto.
You don't give up
easily, do you?
Hey, what's with your face?
(laughing)
Get ready to be sliced
just like an onion.
Or if you prefer,
like a tomato.
(whining)
You're going to have to get
out of the way, children.
Misao, could you take
them someplace safe?
Come on, kids.
Yeah, let's get out of here.
All right, then, who's
gonna be the first one of you
to get shipped back to hell?
Hmm?
What now, sensei?
Well?
♪
I'll be your opponent.
(laughing)
Well, Battousai,
why don't you pull out
your secret sword and show me.
Huh?
(sword unsheathing)
Oh, great, he's
not gonna be able
to bluff his
way out of this.
If I were you I'd
reconsider this foolish whim.
Once I pull out my sword
you will die
a disastrous death.
Have you changed
your mind yet?
My mind's all made up.
Now let's see which
man's going to die.
This is real bad.
He knows that poor man
is a big fake.
(groaning)
Ready, now!
(yelling)
Now, take him out!
Stay here, kids,
I'll be right back.
Don't move.
♪
Watch it, I'm a legend.
(fighting)
Now hold on,
I don't want to fight.
Why?
I'm a, I'm a...
♪
Well, I'm afraid I lied.
I'm not Battousai the Slasher.
Right.
Now don't play jokes,
I am certain you are Battousai
and I am going to kill you.
But I'm really not.
(water gurgling)
Kenshin, this stuff is heavy.
Why'd you have to buy
so much food anyway?
-We needed it.
-Kenshin, come quick.
Those goons from
the restaurant are back
and they've got
a real fighter with them.
Let's go, Misao!
Wait, Kenshin, uh,
what do I do with the radish?
This is it, you're
going to meet your maker.
But I'm telling you,
I'm just a phony.
The fact that you're a fake
doesn't matter to me one bit,
you pathetic old man.
There's something else
a lot more important.
I want to be
the man who's known
as the slayer of
Battousai the Slasher.
Yah!
Aahhh!
Ugh.
♪
Better say your
prayers right now.
(grimacing)
♪
Your life is over!
Who's that?
Kenshin!
Huh?
Don't be stupid,
he'll just kill you.
You're out of
your league here.
(groaning)
What?
(grumbling)
You're impressive,
but not quite enough for me.
Hmm?
♪
Impossible.
Is that a cross marked
scar on his left cheek?
No, it just can't be!
Ahh!
Mitsurugi style!
Ryutsuisen!
Don't kill me!
(whimpering)
Spare my soul!
Battousai, it was really him.
Kenshin's Battousai?
It looks like
it's already over.
I guess we got
here too late.
Well, that's a relief.
So where would you like
these groceries, sensei?
Well, uh--you?
I don't know.
No one makes
fools out of us!
-Huh?
-Look who we've got.
You two better get
the hell out of this place,
or we'll kill these kids.
Go on, get the hell
out of this place
or these brats
are dead meat.
Do you think I'm foolin'?
Just try me, come on,
Battousai, I dare you, come on.
(growling)
No!
Don't do anything stupid!
I swear we will!
Let go of those
little kids
or you're gonna die!
Ahhh!
Take this!
(rocks smashing)
That was pretty darned good.
(heavy breathing)
-Are you all right?
-Sensei!
Those bad men
are never coming back.
I'm just glad
you're all okay.
Huh?
I'm so sorry, Mr. Battousai.
I had no idea
that you were the guy
I was pretending to be.
I hope you'll find it
in your heart to forgive me.
Get up, there's no need
for you to apologize.
But please tell us who are you
and how did you get here?
I'm Heizo Ogawa,
that's my real name.
My dream was to
always be a swordsman,
but I was never
very good at it.
So instead I sold snake oil
and that's when
I met all these kids,
but I didn't have any
money to feed all of them.
I was in a financial bind
and didn't have
any other options.
I had heard about Battousai
from some fellows in town.
I realized that
if I used his name,
I'd be able to make more
money than I normally could,
then at least these kids
would be properly taken care of.
Too bad, snake oil's a blast.
I see, so you put that
old cross mark on your arm.
Of course.
But don't knock
snake oil, it's great!
It will make any wound
heal a lot quicker.
Well, I bet you
haven't used this sword
since you got out of
the snake oil business.
Have you?
That sword is
impossible to pull out.
I'm really sorry.
How come you're sorry,
were you really bad?
He tried to pretend to be
somebody else, that's all.
Shinta, I'm sorry.
My apologies to everyone.
We love you even though
you're not Battousai, Sensei.
You helped us all
and kept us safe from harm.
You're the sensei
we love the most.
We love you, Sensei.
Me too.
You're the most wonderful
sensei in the world.
Promise that you'll
never leave us, please.
Okay, I promise.
Yippie!
Our sensei is the greatest one!
♪
Take care of
yourself, Battousai.
I don't go by
that name anymore.
I'm afraid it's got
too many painful memories.
I go by Kenshin Himura now.
All right, well,
take care, Kenshin.
Thanks, Mr. Ogawa.
You know what?
Even though my old name
isn't something
I want to think about,
I'm glad
it's helped people.
Then I sure hope
you don't get mad
if I happen to use it
when I get into a bind.
What?
Thanks for your help, Kenshin.
Have a good trip.
All right, you kids,
say thank you to our friends.
Thank you, Kenshin,
thank you, everybody.
(kids all saying thank you)
I hope he finds a
better job for their sake.
Anything's better
than snake oil.
Well, you have to admit
he's got a lot of guts.
Yeah, more than
this wimp over here.
Huh?
♪
(kids saying goodbye)
Well, kids, there they go.
Did you happen to notice
that there's no smoke?
That's because
it's a sailing ship.
Our friend Kenshin
is sailing off
to another part of the world.
Ready to meet new
challenges along the way.
I know it's always sad
to say goodbye to friends,
especially friends that really
help us when we need them.
But don't despair.
Kenshin and his friends are
off to yet another adventure.
And we wish them all the
happiness in the world.
♪
What do you say,
let's go home!
Come on, follow me, kids!
Okay, Sensei Heizo.
Hey, call me Sensei Battousai.
(laughing)
♪
(singing foreign language)