♪
(waves crashing)
The final stage of the
plan is about to start.
I've put more than
half of my fortune
into the construction
of this steel-clad warship,
the Rengoku,
and if those three
think they can stop me,
they're sadly mistaken.
A steel-clad ship?
Hmm.
If Shishio is allowed
to carry out his plan,
he might very well succeed
in forcing the surrender
of the Meiji government.
♪
Why do they bother?
They must know
they can't stop me.
Saito Hajime, Battousai Himura.
Hmm...who's the other one?
We only know that he's
a fighter from Kyoto.
Those who've seen him fight
said he's quite good,
but I'm certain that he has
little skill or experience
compared to the other two.
A little fish,
no one to worry about.
(sneeze)
Sorry, I always have to sneeze
before a big fight.
Well, I'm ready if you are.
This is the good guys
against the bad guys, right?
Tell me, Kenshin,
do you think
you'd be able to cut
through that vessel's armor?
Yes, I could.
The part that's above
the water line, anyway.
All right, listen,
I want you to go in
from the starboard side,
and I will enter
from the port side.
And me, what do I do?
You might want
to relax a little,
take yourself a nap.
Hey, Saito, I came here to fight
just like you, you got that?
All right, here's the plan,
now listen closely.
While Saito and I
draw their attention
by attacking from
both sides of the ship,
you look for a small boat to use
to sneak up behind the Rengoku
and destroy it with the
high-explosive grenades.
What?
It's all up to you,
you said you wanted
to be a hero,
well, now's your big chance.
Prepare the Armstrong Cannon for duty.
Cannon loaded and ready, sir!
♪
Fire!
Now, fire!
(boom)
Go!
Ugh!
Hey...
...are you guys all right?
Saito, Kenshin, where are ya?
Now how am I gonna
carry out our plan?
All the small boats
have been blown to bits
thanks to that cannon of theirs!
Bastards!
Huh?
Six five!
Direct hit, sir!
Should we reload the cannon
and fire again, sir?
No, the cannon
will be of no use now,
they'll attack from close range.
Deploy the Gatling gun
and be ready.
Yes, they'll be
here any moment.
Huh?
(splash)
Ugh.
Oh!
♪
Whoa!
I'm surprised that you found me,
that you figured out my plan.
Very impressive,
congratulations.
Since it seems that
you can read my mind,
it should come as no surprise
that I can read yours, as well.
Which is how I know that
you two are merely decoys
and the real attack
has yet to come.
(rolling)
♪
Huh?
Sano!
Let him get closer.
Huh?
Fire!
(machine gun firing)
Yah!
(splash)
Huh?
♪
Super!
Hmph.
Did you see that?
He's even stronger than Anji!
Not such a little
fish after all.
Ahh, gah!
What are those things?
A few small hand grenades
like that can't hurt us!
The sides of this vessel
are constructed
of solid steel armor!
(vaporizing)
(explosion)
Wha-ah!
Oh!
Ahh!
Whoo!
(splash)
You know, the more
I think about it,
the more I think I oughta try
and find some other work.
If it weren't for
the bad guys, I would!
But the bad guys are out there
and I'm the only guy
that can stop them.
I hope you're ready,
Shishio, because here I come,
and then we're gonna see
just how tough you really are.
Now!
(panting)
All section leaders,
be ready to report.
Engine room, what's your status?
The engine is inoperable,
and the screw shaft
has been destroyed!
Destroyed?
The stern's on fire,
we can't contain it!
Boiler room reporting,
we've got major
flooding down here!
The fire's spreading,
it's right outside
the ammunition room!
(crew yelling)
♪
I simply refuse to believe
that this ship
could be destroyed
by one kid with
a few hand grenades!
Ugh!
He wasn't acting alone.
Huh?
Obviously, his surprise
attack is the direct cause
of the Rengoku's destruction.
But the opportunity
for him to succeed,
to be in the right place
at the right time,
with exactly the right weapon
to stop me.
This opportunity was
created by his two allies,
Saito and Battousai.
But my failure is not
their responsibility alone.
The greatest failure of all,
the greatest mistake was mine!
♪
I failed because
I underestimated my enemies,
but I learn from my mistakes.
I know now that I have no choice
but to eliminate
all three of you!
Uh, Shishio,
we should continue
this elsewhere.
The ship is going down.
On one condition.
Condition?
It must be at Mount Hiei
Rukutsurane Shrine Archway,
my stronghold.
♪
That way we can be certain
that no one will disturb us,
just you and the
Juppongatana group,
and we'll settle this
thing once and for all.
♪
Sure, ten of you against
the three of us, right?
That's fine with me, Shishio,
but why not finish it
right now, mano-a-mano?
I'm sure we can settle this
before the ship sinks.
What's up, Kenshin?
♪
As you said, the Rukutsurane
Shrine Archway on Mount Hiei.
We will meet up with you there.
♪
Mr. Shishio,
we must abandon ship,
it will sink any minute now!
♪
Battousai,
as a man of honor,
it will be a pleasure
to settle our differences
one-on-one,
in single combat.
But know this,
nothing and no one
will be allowed
to stand in the way
of my final goal!
I will never
underestimate you again.
♪
I look forward to
our next meeting.
♪
We could destroy
all of those life boats
and the people in them,
including Shishio,
but if we did that,
we'd be guilty
of spilling the blood
of innocent victims.
Because most of them
are just followers
who don't understand
how evil Shishio really is.
If you really believe that
about the Juppongatana group,
then you're even more
naïve than I thought,
which I didn't think
was possible.
Saito, all those people
had a choice which side to be on
and they all chose
the wrong one,
but I think everyone
deserves the opportunity
to choose again.
Ahh!
All right,
Sanosuke Sagara's here,
now you two, tell me
where Shishio is right now!
(pop)
What do you mean he's gone,
come back here, you coward!
Brave, but dumb.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm not finished with you...
Maybe, but you
gotta admit, Saito,
without his help, we couldn't
have beaten Shishio today.
Come back here, you wimp!
Sano's a lot more reliable
than you might think.
...you lily-livered
chicken hearts!
Nothing will change the fact
that he's
aggravating and stupid,
but then again,
he's also a loyal friend
and a courageous fighter.
Come back here, you coward!
Edo is just on the other side
of that far bridge over there.
No flames, no smoke.
It's still safe.
Yeah.
♪
We're still not sure
how many citizens
were killed or injured.
The police force
lost 41 men.
They lost that many?
What a waste.
That's less than one percent
of the policemen who
were defending the town.
Not bad.
Not bad?
Oh yeah,
tell their families that.
Hmm, I've got to get
these reports done
before I can even leave here.
So, why don't you two
wait for me in Aoiya?
I just don't get it,
help me figure this out,
will ya, Kenshin?
Sure, Sano, if I can.
If the three of us,
you, me, and Saito,
are fighting on the same side,
why is it that I still
don't like the guy very much?
I heard that
you were arrested
and had some kind
of run-in with him
while you were in prison.
So, what'd you give him?
Information,
or an apology
for what you did!
Gah!
Uhh...
Do you think I'd apologize
to a guy who would lock me
in a jail cell
for no reason at all?
Once we get through
with Shishio,
I'm gonna make Saito
apologize to me!
I am starving,
hey, what do you say
when we get to Aoiya,
we find a nice inn
and get us some beef hot pot?
Mm-hmm.
Huh?
Hey, guys!
How are ya, Yoshi boy?
Whatcha hanging out here for,
don't you have anything else better to do?
Hanging out, I'm standing guard!
Hey Kori, I've got good news!
Kenshin's come back!
(door sliding)
Ugh, ahh!
What are you being
so sneaky about, huh?
I'm so happy to see you again!
And I hope that you're
glad to see me, too.
Mm-hmm, I am.
I see you did a great
job of guarding Kori,
that was good work, Yoshi.
Thank you, Sano.
Just doing what I
could to help out.
Hey, what happened to Misao,
and the other members
of the Oni gang?
Huh?
Misao isn't well.
(panting)
You here, Misao?
How...
could...
I?
How could I have allowed them
to treat me like that,
to treat me like
a stupid little girl?
I'm an idiot,
a good-for-nothing girl who
doesn't even know how to fight!
Oh, it's my fault, oh!
What happened to her?
We really don't know for sure,
but she's been this way
ever since she fought
that guy yesterday.
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
That's who she's talking about.
Two men who work for Shishio
came through yesterday,
and she got into a big fight
with the one that they call
the Blind Sword.
His name is Usui,
and he's the most
bloodthirsty killer
of them all.
With his animal cunning,
his skill as a fighter,
and his love of killing,
I'm impressed that Misao
even managed to survive
a fight with this guy.
She did, though.
Oh!
Huh?
What are you doing here, Anji?
You know I don't like
to be interrupted.
Killing innocent civilians
serves no purpose, Usui.
Let her go.
Shishio's plan has failed,
it's time to regroup.
So what?
I will kill her
because killing
is what brings me pleasure.
Then I promise you,
as your blade does to her,
mine will do to you.
Come back and kill her
some other time if you must,
but you will not dishonor me
by doing so in my presence.
After that, they didn't say
anything, anything at all,
They just stood there
for a long time
staring at each other.
And then they left.
The other one,
the one called Anji,
there's something about
him that's different
than the other guys
in Shishio's group.
And he must be
one heck of a fighter
or Usui wouldn't have
backed down like that.
Sounds like this Anji
is the one responsible
for saving Misao's life.
But Usui would've
killed her just for fun.
The day we meet, Usui,
will be your last.
Kenshin!
Hmm, what is it, Yoshi?
Well, there's something
that's really important
that we have to talk about.
Aoshi is in Edo.
What?
Yes, and I've got
other news as well.
Yeah, go on.
No, let me tell him.
After all, I'm still
the leader of the Oni gang,
so I consider it my duty
to give Kenshin a full report.
(water dribbling)
(squeeze)
(panting)
Huh?
-Come with me!
-Ow!
Now, you got that?
There's no time to lose!
Okina has regained
consciousness!
I wish I knew what
was going on around here.
He's awake, he's awake!
Okina's awake!
I just can't believe it!
Who'd have thought it?
It looks like he's recovered!
Okina, Okina, are you all right?
(grunting)
(pop)
I'm terribly sorry,
I apologize to you all
for making you worry.
Kenshin, I have a favor to ask,
but first, there are things
I must tell you.
Kenshin, how much do you know
about Aoshi Shinomori?
Does this favor have
something to do with him?
Indeed, it does,
but please,
before you ask me what it is,
allow me to tell you
what has gone before.
I raised Aoshi as if
he were my own son,
and he grew into a good
and honorable man.
He in turn raised Misao
as if she were his daughter,
but when she was
about ten years old,
he suddenly changed into a man
obsessed with one thing
and one thing only,
the need to become
what he calls
the most powerful,
but what I call
a cold-blooded murderer.
Oh!
The favor I ask of you
is to kill
Aoshi Shinomori if you can.
(faint heartbeat)
I raised him,
I gave him everything,
and how did he show
his gratitude?
By savagely attacking me,
by stabbing and slashing
his benefactor so many times
that it's a miracle I survived.
Ugh!
♪
Mr. Aoshi!
Why?
Why did you do it?
♪
Are you going to
kill him, Kenshin?
♪
Will you end his existence?
Will you send him
to a place where
we can no longer be together?
Know what I think?
Murderers ought to die,
but it's in the next world
they'll get
their comeuppance.
Interesting.
Interesting?
For all right-thinking people,
it's the only morally
acceptable point of view!
Aoshi isn't a murderer,
not yet.
Oh!
If Aoshi Shinomori
was truly obsessed,
if he no longer
had human feelings,
if he was the insane,
heartless killer
that you say he is,
then you wouldn't
be standing here.
Even though he
viciously attacked you,
perhaps some part
of him held back,
and that would explain
why you're still alive.
I believe he's sick,
and that this sickness
creates a wall
between his soul
and his heart,
so it's hard for him
to feel much of
anything for anyone.
I can't grant your favor, sir,
but I will bring him
back here if I can.
Together, perhaps
you can heal each other.
I understand.
Hmm?
♪
Oh...
(sobbing)
♪
It'll be all right,
it's okay.
(sobbing)
♪
And to think
I almost destroyed
Misao's happiness forever.
I'm in your debt,
Kenshin Himura.
Kenshin, we just got a message,
it's from Saito!
He says that we're supposed
to leave tomorrow morning
to begin the battle
against Shishio!
Kenshin Himura,
I can't thank you enough.
♪
Kenshin?
Huh?
Oh, hi, Kori.
Shouldn't you get some rest?
It's only a few hours
till dawn, you know.
That's all right,
I've already been asleep
for a while,
a couple of hours.
A couple of hours?
Are you sure that's enough?
And what about you,
what are you doing up this late?
Well, I was lying there,
thinking about--
Ow!
Um, never mind.
It's almost time
for the great battle
to begin, isn't it?
Kenshin, your secret method.
When you're fighting,
is it very dangerous?
I'll be fine, Kori, really.
Don't worry, all right?
You dope!
Of course I'll worry!
Now, answer me!
(giggles)
Well, I'll try.
The secret principle
that my fighting style
is based on is called
Ama Kakeru Ryu no Hirameki,
and what makes it so dangerous
is that if you're not careful
it'll end up controlling you,
rather than the
other way around.
I learned that the hard way,
that's how I earned the name
Battousai the Slasher.
But if I try too hard
to control the power,
my speed and strength
will be compromised
and the technique won't work,
so what I have to do
is concentrate
my energy in a zone
between those extremes, you see?
As long as I'm in that zone,
I'll always win.
♪
Oh.
Megumi asked me
to give you this.
She said that you
should take it with you,
that it'll bring you good luck.
Promise me you'll come
back safely, Kenshin.
If anything were
to happen to you,
I...
♪
Hi-ya!
Ugh!
Yoshi!
What's the matter with you?
You and I gotta talk.
This poor guy's
going into a battle
from which he
could never return,
and all you can do
is talk to him?
The least you could do is
give him a little kiss or two!
Well, what's that look for?
You know just what
I'm talking about!
Yoshi!
You just better mind your
own business, understand?
If you keep being such a brat,
I'm going to tell Tsubame!
Now wait a minute,
she's got nothing
to do with this!
Yoshi, I expect you
to take care of everyone here
while I'm gone.
Hold on!
You mean, I gotta stay home?
Course you do.
I can't risk losing you, Yoshi.
If anything were to
ever happen to you,
who would pay my tab
over at Lenny's restaurant?
Not funny!
Oh.
I am going with you!
There's no reason
why I shouldn't
and a whole lot of
reasons why I should.
I've been in constant training
ever since you left.
I'm a whole lot better fighter
than I was before,
a whole lot better,
believe me!
Yeah, I agree.
That's exactly why
I want you to stay here
and guard the town!
Huh?
You never know
what's going to happen
during a war, I mean,
what if Shishio's
men were to try
and sneak into town
and you weren't there
to sound the alarm
and warn everyone?
You see what I mean?
We've all got a job to do,
and yours is right here,
making sure that
everyone here is safe
until it's over
and I can come back.
There's nothing to worry about.
Nobody has anything
to worry about
as long as I'm around!
And while I'm
looking for Aoshi,
do you think that you
could protect Aoiya?
That's if you see him.
You got it.
So that's why you were crying
so much this afternoon,
so he'd agree
to your deal!
(yelling at each other)
Kenshin!
Kenshin, Misao's right.
Don't worry about Aoiya,
the only thing you
need to think about
is beating the Juppongatana.
Is that all?
Well then, I guess we've
got nothing to worry about!
♪
Tomorrow, I'll begin
the most important battle
of my life.
A battle that has to be fought,
not only to protect the lives
of these wonderful friends
who are depending on me,
but to preserve the freedom
and security of all
the people of Japan.
♪
(birds chirping)
Kenshin, Sano, it's time.
♪
Follow me.
We wouldn't want
to keep Shishio waiting,
would we?
Kenshin?
♪
After you've won the battle,
you and I are going to Kyoto.
I'd like that a lot.
♪
Let's go.