♪
(singing in foreign language)
Our story begins
at a gambling den
where Sanosuke had taken
Kenshin to play dice.
While there, he was told
that his friend Yoita
had died from
an overdose of opium.
The drug was being
distributed on the streets
by the Oni gang,
a criminal family
run by Henry Takeda.
Before Sano could
get any details,
a mysterious girl
named Megumi
rushed into the room
and begged for help.
She was being chased by
thugs from the Oni gang
who were trying to kidnap her.
When Megumi took refuge
in the Kamiya dojo,
Takeda sent his forces
to attack the compound.
He unleashed a giant-size
killer named Hyottoko,
who had the ability
to breathe fire,
and a lethal assassin
named Beshimi
whose favorite weapon
was poisoned darts.
Kenshin and Sanosuke
were able to defend the dojo
but Yoshi was
wounded on the arm
by a poisoned pellet
and became deathly ill.
Megumi told us she was the
only one who could save him.
♪
(loud bang)
Kenshin!
(crying)
Kori, what's happened?
Yoshi is...he's...
It just can't be.
It's impossible.
No!
-You must have made a mistake.
-No way, he can't be dead.
(labored breathing)
The fever seems
to have broken.
I believe it's safe
to say he'll be up
in about a day or so.
(laughs)
I'm tellin' ya, you
scared me half to death.
You came running out like
something bad had happened.
We misunderstood
your message.
You must have been
crying tears of joy.
I was so relieved.
I was petrified that
Yoshi wouldn't make it.
(exclaiming)
Now I'm afraid I won't make it.
I'm so grateful you were
able to come, Dr. Gensai.
You're the best
physician in Kyoto.
If you want to thank someone,
thank the woman that wrote
this prescription.
She must have medical training
in addition to being
an expert in pharmacology.
Everything I needed to create
the antidote is listed here
with instructions on how
to mix the ingredients.
She's amazing but she's
pretty much a mystery.
We don't know her that well.
Her name is Megumi Takani.
So her last name's Takani.
Sounds familiar.
She's very nice.
In fact, I'm beginning
to like her more and more.
♪
(grunting)
Are you telling me
these two boys
beat Hyottoko and Beshimi?
If I didn't know you so well,
I'd say you'd been drinking.
The one with
the scar on his cheek
was the most skillful swordsman
I've ever seen in my life.
It worries me that
we know so little
about someone so skillful.
Find out what you can
and report back.
As you command.
♪
Red hair and a cross
scar on his left cheek.
I wonder...
Could it be?
(birds chirping)
♪
(all gasping)
It's been a very long time
since I made sweet rice cakes.
You can make 'em
whenever you want.
They're the best
ones we've ever seen!
Hey!
What happened to Sanosuke?
He was here a minute ago.
He's been kinda busy lately.
Maybe he went off
to take a rest.
I know he was
so worried about Yoshi
he couldn't get
to sleep last night.
I'm sure he'll
be back here soon.
Whoa!
Look, there's no sense
waiting for him.
I think we should
celebrate Yoshi's recovery.
All in favor say "rice cake"!
Rice cake!
Oh!
(mumbling)
They're great!
Yay!
Yoshi, you should be
careful how much you eat.
You know, you're not
100 percent recovered yet.
I'm not falling
for that trick.
You're just trying to get
some more of these babies
for yourself!
Aw, forget it!
I admit it, you're right.
Hey, Megumi, would you
mind showing me the secret
to making those
great rice cakes?
I'd love to, it's really easy.
Well, I'm glad
to hear you say that.
Then I'll make the next batch.
Rice cakes made by Kori,
I can hardly wait!
I better call the hospital now
to make an appointment
to have my stomach pumped.
(laughing)
Apparently, we
weren't able to get
all the poison
out of your system.
Your mouth still works.
Do you mind,
I'm trying to eat here!
You better go shave,
you grew a huge beard!
And hurry before we
all gobble you up!
(laughing)
Oh, Suzie.
This is great,
I'm really enjoying it.
It's like being with
a wonderful family.
If this girl was
really my sister,
I think I'd ask
my parents to disown me!
If Yoshi was my brother,
I'd go to court and beg to
be declared an only child.
(groaning)
You two might as well
adopt each other,
you already fight
like you're related.
(laughing)
-Megumi?
-Hm?
Does your family
live here in Kyoto?
I don't have a family anymore.
What?
Well, I think I'll
go make some tea.
How awful for her.
I wonder what happened to them.
(water pouring)
Everyone here has been
treating me so nicely.
Yes, and I see
you figured out a way
to express your gratitude.
(gasps)
But how are you
going to explain
that you brought
drugs into this house?
I found opium in your room!
♪
Oh dear.
So are you pushing
drugs for those men
who were trying to kidnap you?
Huh, is that what
this is all about?
No.
I made that opium.
I see it all now.
You're the source
of these drugs.
You're the reason
my friend died!
Wait a minute, Sanosuke.
We have to give her
a chance to explain.
Are you producing opium
for some medical reason?
I might be able to answer that.
You wouldn't happen to be
the daughter of Takawa Takani,
would you?
What?
How do you know
my father's name?
Okay, now it's Suzie's turn.
I don't know what to do.
She's got you
boxed in, all right.
Hmm.
I thought your name
sounded familiar.
The Takani family of Aizu
has a long and proud history
of turning out great doctors.
But six years ago,
they became involved
in a war with the imperial army.
Takawa Takani was
killed in the struggle
and the family home
was burned to the ground.
Mrs. Takani and her two sons
were thought to have died
in the fire.
According to reports,
only one young daughter
survived the attack.
It must have been awful for you.
I imagine the pain can
be overwhelming at times.
The loss of my
family is something
I will always carry in my heart
but it's nothing compared to
what happened to me afterwards.
♪
I came to Kyoto from
Aizu five years ago
and became a live-in
assistant to a local doctor.
I found out later
that the doctor
was tied in to the Oni gang.
He was making opium
for Takeda to distribute.
But the doctor got greedy.
He started selling
opium on the side
and they killed him
and then they forced me
to take his place.
That explains a lot.
Huh?
I always worked hard
to be a great doctor
like my father,
but I feel I've disgraced him.
Instead of helping people,
I made something that
took over their souls
and finally killed them.
I've wanted to commit
suicide so many times,
but the truth is,
I didn't have the courage.
You had the courage
to escape from Takeda.
What happened that
finally made you run away?
I was forced to create
a new kind of opium
which could be mass
produced inexpensively.
There's no telling how
much damage it will cause.
I couldn't stand it, so I took
what I had made and ran off.
Since you're the
only person who knows
how to produce this new opium,
you're a valuable commodity.
If Takeda gets you back,
he'll lock you up in a lab
and force you to turn out
this poison by the ton.
We'll never let
that happen, Megumi!
We'll protect you
from that monster,
I swear.
You better stay inside
the compound for a while.
From what we know
of these guys,
they're not gonna give
you up without a fight.
Thank you all.
♪
You shouldn't blame
yourself for the bad things
that happened to you.
Sometimes,
no matter what we do,
we're a victim of circumstances
and we have to struggle
to pull ourselves out.
Most of us know exactly what
you've been going through.
Let me tell you, I've been
on my own for a while,
but I found ways to adapt.
You have to create
a new family
to replace the one that's gone
and that's what we've
done here at the dojo.
Would you like to
join our family?
-Really?
-Mm-hm.
-Oh, brother.
-What's the matter?
I can't believe how quickly
you're willing to invite
this woman to join us!
Call me stubborn,
but one of my friends died
because of her poison.
(gasps)
Oh.
He's still in pain.
He's having a hard time
adjusting to the loss
of his friend.
You just have to
be patient with him.
I'm sure he'll
come around eventually.
(crying)
Well, it's just for
a couple of days.
I'll ask my mother...
(birds chirping)
Come and play with us,
Megumi, and we'll have fun!
Yumi and I invented
some really great games.
All right, as soon
as I finish this.
Hooray!
Yahoo!
-Hurry up!
-Come on!
(chuckling)
(gasps)
♪
Hello, you seem to be
in a big hurry, young lady.
I don't mean to be nosey,
but perhaps I can help you
with something.
-No, thanks.
-I see.
Well, even though there's
nothing I can do for you...
there's something
you can do for me.
And I won't take
no for an answer.
Han'nya!
Mr. Takeda is waiting for you.
♪
What the--
You've crossed the line.
♪
You won't be harmed.
I promised you safe
passage in my letter.
Besides, what good would
it do me to harm you?
I'm much more interested
in having you come back
to work for me.
When you get to know me better,
you'll find I'm a
most forgiving man.
Oh sure, especially
when you're going
to make millions off my opium.
I must admit,
it's a consideration,
but after all I've invested,
does it surprise you?
What brought all this on?
You seemed perfectly
happy until last week.
What?
I only worked for you because
I couldn't kill myself.
It's true.
I hoped one day
to have enough money
to buy my way out of this mess
and go start a family
to replace the one I lost.
That dream is
what kept me going.
It's the kind of
dream we all have.
And I'm sure we'll be able
to accommodate you later.
There won't be any later.
I've made up my mind.
Really?
I don't care if
I have a family again.
I'd rather die than
have thousands of people
get hooked on this new opium.
I refuse to make any more!
Then, my dear, you
most certainly will die.
But you won't die alone.
They'll find you
buried in the ashes
of the Kamiya dojo
alongside the charred
bodies of several adults
and two or three small children.
You're an evil man.
No, I'm just a man
who's prepared to do
whatever's necessary
to protect his investment.
If you won't work for me,
I can't have you out there
working for somebody else.
And accidents do happen.
(chuckling)
I'll kill him.
♪
Let me clue you in to
the facts of life, my dear.
You can't get away.
You can't even choose
to take your own life
unless you want others
to die with you.
Just admit you're in a corner
and give up this game.
What we had wasn't so bad.
Why don't you come
back on your own
and everything will
be like it was
before all this
unpleasantness ever happened.
I think you'll come
to your senses.
And if you don't, remember,
household accidents
kill more people
than heart attacks.
So, why didn't you just
drag her back to headquarters
and be done with it?
Are you afraid of someone
in their compound?
Maybe Henry Takeda
isn't strong enough
to overcome
Battousai the Slasher.
I don't need any more trouble
than we already have
in this situation.
If they think Megumi
has left of her own free will,
I doubt even Battousai
will try to interfere
with her decision.
He's just a hired assassin,
there's no reason for him to
move against our organization.
Yeah?
I wouldn't bet on it.
Boss, I think someone
was spying on us
here in the woods.
Don't worry about it.
The only enemy
we're concerned with
is a man named Kenshin Himura,
also known as
Battousai the Slasher.
I'll keep watch, sir.
(sobbing)
♪
I just can't get away.
I'll never escape from Takeda
or his opium
or being responsible
for thousands of deaths.
(sobbing)
♪
Megumi, your bath is ready!
Megumi?
Are you there?
♪
Oh.
Kenshin!
Megumi's run off!
How can you be sure?
She left me a letter
saying she's going back.
-To Aizu?
-Well, that's very rude.
She could have at least said
goodbye before she took off.
I didn't even have a chance to
thank her for saving my life.
It doesn't make sense to me.
Why would she go back there?
She wouldn't.
Her family's gone,
so what would be the point?
It's a lie.
♪
I thought you'd show up here.
What will you accomplish
by going back to them?
Maybe nothing at all,
but don't worry, I won't
be making any more opium
and killing innocent people.
That much I can promise.
You know Takeda will
never accept that.
He'll force you.
That's my problem
to deal with.
You'd best leave me alone.
I've gotta go, I can't talk.
Why are you in such
a hurry to die?
I know what threat
Takeda used on you
and neither I nor Kenshin will
allow any member of our dojo
to be harmed.
Yes, but--
You have a family
waiting for you
back at the dojo.
And for all I know, your
real family is alive somewhere
and waiting for you, too.
It's too late.
Even if I knew where
to find my real family,
I'd be too ashamed
to look them in the eye.
Their baby, who held
so much promise,
is just a common criminal.
No matter how hard I try,
I'll never be able
to rise above my past.
Stop acting like the
world has come to an end.
(gasps)
This may surprise you,
but you're not the
only person in this life
who carries around a lot
of shame from her past.
Sacrificing your life isn't
going to bring back my friend
or erase the guilt,
but if you stay alive,
you might be able
to do something
to make up for it.
You can finish your schooling,
become a doctor,
make a difference
in this world
by saving lives
instead of taking them.
Watch out!
♪
I'm impressed.
There aren't too many
people whose reflexes
are quick enough
to dodge my blow.
What is your problem?
(grunting)
♪
I don't have a problem, you do!
I'm the guardian of this house.
The name's Shikijo.
Turn over the woman to us
right now and go away
or I'll break your body
into little pieces.
♪
All right.
(grunting)
♪
Why don't you come down here
and face me man to man
if you think you're so tough?
Or are you scared?
Nice try, brat, but
it'll take more than that
to provoke me.
You're about to
learn a hard lesson.
This fight is gonna
last for two hits.
I'm gonna hit you and
you're gonna hit the ground.
(yelling)
♪
Come on, kid, let's do it!
You're through!
(yelling)
♪
Is that the best you can do?
So far I'm not even
breaking a sweat,
but now you're about
to see my true power.
♪
He's unbelievably strong.
(laughing)
♪
I'm not through with you yet.
Better give up, kid.
I'm impressed that your
skull is still together
after one of my headbutts.
But the tissue inside
has been damaged.
The shock to your brain
will begin to affect
your whole body
in a few minutes.
I doubt you'll even be able
to control your fingers.
Over the years, I've
trained in and mastered
every single form
of martial arts.
My body is a
completely lethal weapon.
I've never been beaten
in hand-to-hand combat
and you don't have what it takes
to challenge me now.
You are nothing but
hot air and big talk.
(laughing)
I'll show you some mercy
and make it quick.
Ready?
(yelling)
No.
(grunting)
What is this?
I can't believe he
still has the strength
to put up a fight.
You think you're the strongest,
but I know you're not.
Kenshin's the one.
You'll find out I'm
telling the truth
if you live to face him.
You're just a lowlife scumbag
who works for a bunch of crooks!
We'll never give in
to someone like you!
I'll have a picnic
on your grave!
Big talk for someone
that's about to die.
(groaning)
That's what I like about
these hard-headed bozos.
They always have
a weak spot somewhere
and they never think
you'll find it.
(groaning)
♪
All right, we can go.
Hm?
Ya!
Come back, you freak!
You don't mind if we
take the girl, do you?
-Sano!
-Huh?
Are you all right?
You look hurt.
I'm fine, don't worry about me.
Help Megumi.
(laughing maniacally)
He's going inside!
Takeda threatened to
kill everyone in the dojo
if she didn't come back to him.
That's the reason she ran off.
I figured it must have
been something like that.
We have to go in and
get her no matter what!
She's part of our family.
She saved my life
when I was injured,
now I'm gonna go save hers!
Good for you!
Let's go show those lowlifes
what we're made of!
I'm in.
You up to it, Sano?
(groaning)
-Let's go!
-Then we're all ready.
-They haven't got a chance!
-We'll show 'em!
Good.
Let's save her.
Hang on, Megumi!
♪
(singing in foreign language)