♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪
Kenshin!
Where are you?
Kenshin, are you in here?
No.
Huh?
Where is he?
He's not here.
(crying)
♪
Why?
Kenshin, why?
(crying)
♪
That Kenshin left without
so much as a goodbye.
What a bastard he is!
Now calm down, Sano.
Otherwise you'll
completely destroy
our entire restaurant.
He's scaring me.
I'm going to go to Ito
and give that damn
snake in the grass
a piece of my mind!
I'm so furious at that Kenshin!
That's a good idea.
Why don't you leave right away?
Why don't you pay your bill
and be on your way?
I don't have any money.
But what about the damages?
I'm still kinda scared.
What a bunch of cheapskates.
You got a lot of nerve, Sano.
If you wanna borrow
money from people
then you shouldn't go around
breaking up their
place, you know?
It's all Kenshin's fault
that I lost my temper in there.
He broke his word when he
didn't say goodbye to me.
So now don't forget, pal.
If you ever leave make
sure you let me know
where you're going,
all right, Kenshin?
Mhmm.
Ah!
Boy, he's really mad.
I should say so.
I guess that he's
really aggravated
about Kenshin leaving here
and not saying goodbye to him.
I never thought Kenshin
would go back to wandering,
I always thought he would
stay here at Kaoru's dojo.
Don't you think Kaoru's
sad about him leaving, too?
Hey!
Huh?
Hi, Yoshi.
Hello.
Have you two seen
Sanosuke anywhere?
He was just here.
Dismantling the restaurant.
So how is Kaoru
handling the bad news?
I'm afraid not so good.
She seems to be
totally out of it.
She's the only one that Kenshin
actually said goodbye to.
(crying)
♪
Please don't be sad, children.
Kenshin will come back.
You'll see.
♪
Kaoru, thank you for everything.
Goodbye.
I must go.
I know how she feels,
but I've never seen anything
affect her like this before.
She hasn't eaten
anything in days
since Kenshin went away.
I thought if I could
get some of her friends
to come over here
and cheer her up
it might snap her out of it.
Can I count on you?
Of course, we'll come
cheer her up right away.
There's enough in this envelope
to get you all the way to Ito.
Thanks a lot, Tsukioka.
I really appreciate it.
I'll pay ya back when I return.
Don't worry, I
don't expect it back.
Give me your hand.
What is that?
Consider it a going away gift.
Tiny explosives.
But I...
I thought you were out
of the explosive business.
What are you doing having
these things around anyway?
Don't worry about it,
they're just for protection.
Be very careful, Sanosuke.
Ito may be a lot more dangerous
than even you
realize it might be.
Oh, yeah?
Then do you know what's
going on with Shishio?
Don't take newspaper
sources lightly.
Don't write about it.
This is a huge underground
assassination organization,
it's not safe to cross them
or get in their way.
I won't.
Who'd believe that
this ghost from the past
is planning to start a war
of vengeance on this country?
No one would believe it.
Well, I better go.
Just watch your back, Sano.
Bye.
Yoshi.
Where have you been?
How can you just run off
and leave us all alone
at a time like this?
Kaoru's a mess and
I need your help.
Yoshi.
You've been followed.
Where do you think you're going?
It's none of your
business where I'm going.
What's it to ya?
I just hope that
for Battosai's sake
you're not planning
to go to Ito.
You see, it's the law of warfare
that you strike at the
weakest part of your opponent.
If you do go to Ito
then Shishio will
surely come after you.
Battosai, in his
present condition,
will not be able to
protect all of you.
You are his weak link.
That's why he left
without telling you.
I don't believe you.
Battosai doesn't want you there,
can't you understand that?
You'll only get him killed
if you go after him.
♪
Is he telling me the truth?
Is that why he left
without saying goodbye?
He thought I'd get in his way?
I went through a great deal
to get Battosai to realize
what I'm saying is the truth.
If you guys go to Ito
you put him in danger.
Stay out of the way
and don't go near him.
Stay here in Kyoto.
Forget it!
Huh?
Hearing what you have to say
makes me wanna go there
even more than ever.
I don't know who
you think you are,
but stay out of my way!
I'd say the same advice
would make sense for you.
Ahhhh!
Ah!
♪
Ahhhh!
You fight dirty.
You have no honor.
Only a cowardly fighter like you
would keep attacking
an injury like that.
Hm?
I told you.
It's the law of warfare
to keep attacking your
opponent's weakest point.
There's no such thing as dirty.
What is about to begin in Ito
is a battle of survival.
It's no place for
youngsters like you.
Stay put here in
Kyoto, little boy.
Don't go to Ito.
Do you understand me?
Aw, forget you!
I see.
Yoshi.
Katsu.
Stay out of it.
My shoulder doesn't hurt.
What really hurts is
that Kenshin thought
that I'd get in his way.
That hurts more than anything.
Kenshin is my friend,
I'll never be in his way.
Now get out or I'll
clean your clock!
Stay out of my way.
Hear me, Saito.
I'm going to shove
off now for Ito.
My fists will be
of some use there.
Sano, you tell him!
Yeah.
You really think your
fists will be helpful to him?
As a matter of fact I do.
Really?
You can't fight your
way out of a paper bag.
Oh, yeah?
Don't let him get to you.
♪
You think you're a good fighter?
I'll put my sword down.
Let me see how good you are.
You and me, mano e mano.
Don't you dare trust him, Sano.
He's a dirty, cheating dog
and he'll do
anything to trick you.
Well, you don't trust
me very much, do you?
Hell no.
Don't you worry.
I assure you I'll fight fairly.
I have no reason to
want to trick you.
But even you,
with your limited
brain capacity,
will realize that
when I beat you
your lack of skill is a
liability Kenshin can't afford.
Yeah, we'll see.
He's good.
I didn't even know that
he could fight like that.
I can't seem to
penetrate his defenses.
Every time I go
for his face or body
he blocks me with
a little effort.
This guy's like a machine.
Sooner or later he's
gotta drop his guard.
And when he does, pow,
I'll have him.
He can't go on
like this forever,
he's got to be tired by now.
♪
I hope that you
have more than that
because your pathetic boxing
is really boring.
He's not even fazed.
That guy's unbelievable.
I've never seen
fighting like that before.
I'm very patient.
You can't last
forever, you know.
You won't do much damage
if you can't get a punch in.
Oh, yeah?
This guy's too good.
He's got the stamina
of a race horse.
I can't get a punch in,
and yet I can't block
one of his punches.
Who the hell is this guy?
Ahhhh!
Poor Sano.
I hate to say it,
but it looks like
Sano's no match for him.
I don't even know if
Kenshin could beat him.
You got it now?
You don't even come
close to me or Battosai
and you're not in our league
and you don't have
our skill or experience
or anything else
for that matter.
To us you're nothing
but a hindrance,
someone that gets in the way.
Oh, shut up.
You can still move?
You're not so bad.
Don't care what you say.
I said I'm going to go to Ito.
Guess again.
You're not going to go anywhere.
Oh, no.
He doesn't have his sword,
but he's in the fang stab pose.
Sano, get out of his way,
he's about to attack you!
He can't do that.
He's barely standing as it is.
He can hardly move,
let alone deflect an attack.
No matter how strong
you think you are,
you're not strong enough.
I'm still standing.
Not for long.
Oh!
How's this, you bastard?
What the...
Do you like that?
I'm strong enough to crush
your arm like a walnut,
how does that feel, huh?
Still think I'm annoying?
You insect.
You and Kenshin were
not born masters.
This is something you become.
Don't underestimate me.
Why you!
It's over.
What?
It's a waste of my time
to try and convince
someone like you.
If you wanna go to
Ito that badly then go.
Nothing I do or say
will change your mind,
so go ahead and
get yourself killed.
Come back here!
You know, conceited
people like you
don't last very long anyway
because you don't
know the basics
of defense or strategy.
Have a nice trip.
Your days are numbered.
Looks like you won, Sanosuke.
Yeah, you defeated him.
You gotta be kidding,
that guy kicked my butt.
Yeah, I guess that he did.
Anyway, let's take care
of your wounds right now.
We really should patch
up that shoulder of yours.
Yeah.
Interesting.
When he was fighting with me
he didn't touch my shoulder.
He completely avoided it,
even when he threw
his first punch.
It was as if he was fighting me
at my level of skill.
He could have easily made
chopped salad out of me,
but he didn't for some reason.
That must be the power
of a Shinsen leader.
This is no time to be resting,
I've gotta get going.
Don't go, we've got to
take care of your wounds.
I'll be okay.
Yoshi, take care of
everything, will ya?
Make sure you take Kaoru
to Kenshin, all right?
I'm counting on
ya, little buddy.
Uhhuh.
I'm going to get stronger
and better, I've got to.
You're only going
to get in his way.
Can't you understand that?
In his way.
I am going to be stronger
by the time I reach Ito.
Kaoru, so how are you feeling?
Oh.
Maybe she's feeling better.
Is she here?
Hm, I wonder
where she's gone to.
Look, her kimono's still here.
You're right, she's gotta
be somewhere around here.
You think we should
go look for her?
I think that's a
good idea, let's go.
Okay.
♪
I don't know why.
I don't really understand it.
But when he said goodbye to me
I just couldn't bear to
hear him say those words.
So I just went into this fog.
And I still can't
snap myself out of it.
Oh, Kenshin,
Kenshin, why did you
have to leave, why?
Why, why?
♪
Kaoru, are you all right?
What's the matter?
♪
Wow, that Saito's
really an awesome fighter,
but so is Sano.
I promised him that I'll
get Koaru to Ito and I will,
even if I have
to drag her there.
Yoshi.
Hm?
Megumi.
Oh, you're still here?
I thought I heard that
you were going to Ito.
So are you going to stay here
and watch the dojo?
Oh, I guess that
you haven't heard,
but Kaoru's still at the dojo.
Huh?
It's not very good,
but you have to eat
something, Kaoru.
Try a bite.
I don't want it.
Don't say that, Koaru,
Tsubame went to a lot of
trouble to make it for you.
Just try some.
No thank you.
You've really gotta
snap out of it.
It's not healthy for
you to act like this.
Just try some, will you?
Please?
Come on, Kaoru.
I just told you.
I don't want it.
Please try some.
I just told you
that I'm not hungry!
Just leave me alone!
Leave me alone.
I can't believe it.
Yoshi told me you
were still at the dojo.
Just what do you want, Megumi?
Well, actually I
just wanted to drop by
and see how you were doing
after Kenshin dumped you.
(laughing)
Please, Megumi.
You don't know what it
feels like to be hurt.
Yes, I do.
But you don't see me
laying around all day crying
and feeling sorry for myself.
I don't feel like
doing much of anything.
I just want you
to leave me alone.
So you don't wanna do
much of anything, huh?
If you could have
anything right now
what would you wish for?
I'd wish for Kenshin.
Then you should go to him.
I can't do that.
Maybe you're afraid that Kenshin
doesn't want you hanging
around, is that it?
I made some secret
medicine for Kenshin.
He told me last time I gave him
some that it worked very well.
Considering what's been going on
he could really use
some of this right now.
But I guess I can't ask a
crybaby like you to deliver it.
So I'll ask Yoshi.
And I'm sure that when
Kenshin gets this medicine
he'll remember me.
Even if he forgets
all about you.
Then tell me, why don't
you go all the way to Ito
and deliver it to him in person.
Do it yourself!
I'm afraid I can't.
I'm not lazy like you
and I have patients
to attend to.
I can't just leave
whenever I want to.
I have responsibilities.
Oh, your patients are more
important than Kenshin.
I guess that proves
that your feelings
don't really amount
to much, do they?
Oh!
Kaoru, you really should
be careful what you say.
I'm still the master of
the Kamiya Kasshin School.
Don't underestimate my ability.
Could we go home, right now?
Don't you dare
underestimate me, either.
I want you to look at me.
I became a doctor
to help others,
do you understand?
And as a way to make
up for my past crimes.
This is the path that
I've chosen to take
and it was Kenshin
who was responsible
for leading me to
this path I'm on.
I have him to
thank for everything.
Dying will not bring
those people back to life.
I can do better by using
my sword to help others.
I try to help as many as I can,
that's how I try to make amends.
You have a knowledge
of medicine,
it's a gift that could
save many people's lives.
You could help a lot of people.
Even more than the
sword of Battosai.
Become a doctor, Megumi.
Aid all the people that
are suffering, Megumi.
They all need your help.
Not just the ones
who suffer from opium,
but the wounded
and the ones with diseases.
Please, Megumi.
Kenshin.
That's the reason that
even if Kenshin isn't around
I still have to take
care of the sick.
That's how I keep my
feelings alive for him.
You're just sitting there
feeling sorry for yourself,
don't you dare presume to
know how I feel about him.
At least I'm doing something.
What are you doing, huh?
What?
What are you going
to do now, Kaoru, cry?
You're hopeless.
I really thought you were
a lot stronger than this.
You really don't
understand, do you, Megumi?
Kenshin told me to my
face he was going to leave,
he said goodbye to me.
Now do you understand
why I hurt so bad?
No, I don't.
Because you don't
know how I feel.
At least he said goodbye to you.
But he left here without
saying anything to me.
Nothing at all.
Instead of just sitting
around here all day crying
you should realize how
you really feel about him.
♪
Maybe she's right.
(footsteps)
Are you finished
talking to her yet?
Yes.
Here, Yoshi, take this.
Okay.
(crying)
Don't worry, Megumi.
We'll find him and
bring him back alive.
All right?
We'll be back soon,
please don't cry.
Okay.
♪
You don't know how I feel.
At least he said goodbye to you.
But he left here without
saying anything to me.
Nothing at all.
Then tell me,
why don't you go
all the way to Ito
and deliver it to him in person.
Do it yourself!
I will.
Kaoru, what are you waiting for?
We have to leave now, hurry up.
What do you mean?
We have to go to Ito.
Yoshi.
Come on, there's a
reason you're the only one
that Kenshin said goodbye to.
Huh?
Hey, don't you understand?
Saying goodbye to you was the
hardest thing Kenshin had to do,
you're the one person he really
wanted to see before he left.
Listen to me,
you're the only one
who can bring
Kenshin back to us.
You're the one he
cares about the most.
I talked to Megumi and she said
she would take care of
the dojo while we were gone.
In exchange she wants you to
hand this medicine to Kenshin.
So will you come?
I need an answer
right now, Kaoru.
I guess.
I guess so.
That's wonderful.
Wow, that's great.
♪
I need him.
I want him.
Kenshin, I need to see you.
Great, let's get moving.
Here.
♪
Oh, Kenshin.
I'll see you in Ito.
Tell him how you really feel.
I hope you'll bring
Kenshin back to us.
Have a wonderful trip, Kaoru.
Come on, slowpoke, we gotta go.
I'll be waiting for you.
♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪