(theme music)
♪
In our last episode
at Shishio's Edo fortress,
Sojiro informed his master
that Kenshin and Saito
were on their
way towards Edo
and would be
arriving shortly.
As Shishio
relaxed in his spa,
he and the paramour Ayumi
made plans for their
guests' arrival
and talked about how
to best take advantage
of the situation.
Knowing that Kenshin
is one of Japan's
greatest swordsmen
and that a confrontation
with him is inevitable,
Shishio wants to find a way
to observe Kenshin in battle
in order to learn his
strengths and weaknesses.
With Ayumi's help
and Sojiro's input,
Shishio comes up with a
scheme to achieve this goal.
He decides to use his
most ferocious assassin,
the brutal giant Senkaku.
♪
(footsteps)
Ah, Mr. Himura, Mr. Saito,
I am Sojiro, welcome.
I know that voice.
Those who betray
my master, Shishio,
don't stay alive
for very long.
♪
Be very careful, Saito.
This is the guy who
killed Sir Okubo.
Oh, come now,
me, an assassin?
I'm just a guide.
A sword would be too
heavy for me to carry.
(chuckling)
My master knows
you're here
and is waiting inside.
Welcome to Edo.
If this is a trap, there's
not much we can do about it.
Come on.
♪
Eiji, wait.
I can take care of myself,
just leave me alone!
You can't go in there.
But I have to.
Senkaku killed my family.
He murdered them
in cold blood.
My poor parents
and my brother
were innocent and they
hadn't done anything wrong,
but he killed
them anyway.
♪
It's up to me now
to avenge all
their deaths.
I know how you feel,
but this fortress
is protected
by a whole division
of Shishio's ninjas.
If you go in there
without any plan,
you'll end up
getting captured
and probably tortured.
You'll never find
Senkaku that way.
Well, I can't just stand
here and do nothing.
I've got to avenge
their deaths.
You just leave everything
to me, all right?
I've never told
you this before,
but I was a member
of the Oni gang.
The Oni?
Wabanshu?
Yeah, let me
just show you.
(owl hooting)
What are you
gonna do with that?
Just wait for my signal,
then follow me, all right?
Huh?
Uh!
(whooshing)
What was that?
Search the grounds!
Come on!
(yelling)
Shh!
-See anyone?
-Not yet, sir.
It was probably an owl.
Great, now we can
sneak in behind them.
Cool.
(grunting)
♪
Would you like a
cool drink, Shishio,
it's quite refreshing.
They've come.
♪
Your name is Shishio
Makoto, I'm told.
Hmm, most strangers
call me Mr. Makoto.
Some would say
you're impolite.
They might at that.
People say a lot
of things about me.
You better be careful.
It sounds like things
are heating up already.
If given a good
enough reason,
Kenshin could kill him with
one stroke of his sword.
I don't think he'll try.
As an invited guest
in his enemy's home,
he's too honorable to pull
a sneak attack unlike you.
Hmm.
What did you attack
the village for?
Your goal is
national domination,
your target Japan itself,
why concern yourself
with a small village?
Hot springs.
Huh?
♪
There are therapeutic
minerals in the water here
that help soothe
the pain of my burns.
But if I were to allow
other guests here,
they would see me and
it would frighten them
so I made it my
own private spa.
You destroyed
an entire village
just because you like
to use its hot springs?
(laughing)
♪
I'm kidding,
I'm just kidding.
Know what your
problem is, Himura?
You don't have
a sense of humor.
And I suppose you do?
You're about as funny as a
pile of dead maggots, friend.
(gasping)
Hey, be quiet!
(owl hooting)
-Why, you, I oughta.
-It won't happen again.
They say if you sneeze,
someone's talking about you.
Oh, I hope it's Aoshi.
I took this village because
I needed a military base
to control the
surrounding area.
The hot springs turned
out to be a bonus.
Bastard.
Not just yet,
my friend.
Now let me get
this straight.
You're gonna use
this fort as a base
while trying to
topple the government?
Mr. Saito, I remember
when you were captain
of the Shinsengumi.
I have so much more in common
with you than Mr. Himura,
I thought you'd
understand my intentions.
I guess I was wrong.
-Go on.
-Ten years ago,
when Mr. Himura was
still remembered
as Battousai the Slasher,
I succeeded him as the
government's shadow assassin.
I was their
loyal servant,
I worked hard,
obeyed every command.
But I learned more
with each new assignment
until I knew so many of
the government's secrets
that they decided to
protect themselves
by having me eliminated.
(guns firing)
♪
They set me on fire to
make sure I was dead.
(screaming)
Almost every inch of
my body was charred,
but my anger within grew
hotter than the flames
and that kept me alive.
Now I carry that
heat with me,
a heat so intense,
it would be unbearable
to living things
if I didn't keep
it under control.
It's like a
reminder of hell
still burning inside me.
I'll have my
revenge someday.
Waiting will
make it sweeter.
In a strange way,
I appreciate what
they did to me.
These wounds
have taught me
my life's most
important lessons,
which are now
ingrained within my heart.
If I trust, I'll be betrayed,
if I let down my
guard, I'll be killed,
I can protect my life only by
taking the lives of others,
and that a desirable man
will remain no
matter what happens
and he will attract
beautiful women
all his life.
(chuckling)
Well, then sounds to me
like you've got it made.
Why don't you
just stay here?
Believe me, I'm tired of
having to track you down.
It'd make my job
a whole lot easier.
I'm confused,
truly I am.
We all lived through the
end of the Tokugawa Era.
I simply don't understand.
♪
What is it that made
you so different from me?
♪
The end of the
Tokugawa Shogunate
was a disaster.
The entire country was in
danger of falling apart.
Civil war raged everywhere,
in the countryside
and in the cities,
between the royalist
loyal to the Emperor
and those who wanted the
power of the government
to remain in the
hands of the Shogun.
I'd think that any
man who had witnessed
the fear and confusion of
that time would want to see
his country under
control again,
that they would do what was
necessary to reunify Japan.
♪
Meanwhile, the government
tried to assassinate me.
By the time I had
recovered from my burns,
the disturbance was over
and the Meiji government
was now in control.
Of course, they
wanted me dead too,
but the Meiji government
was too weak to get it done.
Can a country be run by a
government as weak as that?
No!
♪
Mediocrity
and complacency
cannot be allowed
to rule Japan.
I'll make the
country strong again.
Total and supreme
control will be mine alone!
Now do you understand the
righteousness of my destiny?
♪
But what about the
people who don't care
if you're right or wrong,
who want to live peacefully?
Their pain for your
ambition with their blood.
♪
Survival of the fittest,
life's most basic law.
The righteousness of
my path is undeniable.
I'm stubborn, I guess,
because I don't believe
it for one second,
and I can't let
innocent people
go on dying
because of you.
Got it?
So, Mr. Saito,
what about you?
Well, now.
The way I feel has nothing
to do with such noble ideas.
It's very simple.
I'd just feel a whole
lot more comfortable
without Shishio around.
If it's a
fight you want,
then it's a
fight you'll get.
But I don't think
we should rush to get
to the main
event quite yet.
First, there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
Huh?
I was the one
responsible
for destroying the
Shingetsu Village.
♪
(chuckling)
Gentlemen, may I
introduce Mr. Senkaku?
If you're responsible for the
destruction of the village,
then you're the one who
murdered Eiji's parents.
So what, punk?
You're dead!
Ya!
He's quick.
You've had it!
(yelling)
(laughing)
Poor man, I thought he'd
last longer than that.
Hey, you can go ahead
and stick a fork in
this guy, he's done.
I promised Eiji.
Hmm?
♪
(grunting)
(gasping)
You then your boss,
that's what I
promised him.
♪
You're history,
dead meat kid!
♪
-Yeah?
-Afraid so.
I killed 99 men so far
and they're all a lot
stronger than you.
You'll make it
an even 100.
(yelling)
♪
Ninety-nine people.
Hmm, that is an
awful lot of people.
(yelling)
♪
Whoa.
Kenshin is as
quick as people say.
But when it
comes to speed,
there isn't anybody
who can match Senkaku.
♪
Now die!
(yelling)
Wow.
Hey.
Is that the only thing
you know how to do?
Anybody who was
fast on his feet
could slip around
behind his opponent.
Even someone who's...
...a really big
guy like me.
We're equally quick,
but I also have physical
strength and stamina
you can't hope to match.
My crescent blades will slice
you into pieces so small,
there won't be enough
left of you to bury!
(yelling)
♪
(grunting)
(owl hooting)
Whoa.
Their security's a lot
tougher than I thought.
There's gotta be a
way to get in there.
Got to,
otherwise I'll
never find Senkaku.
Don't worry,
I'll find a way.
Sneaking into places is
one of the specialties
of the Oni gang so
it'll be easy for me
'cause I'm not
scared of anything,
except for...
...big, hairy spiders!
Misao, quiet!
What was that?
What are you scared of?
(squealing)
Spider?
There's someone
in the woods.
That's just great, now
we're gonna get caught.
My one weakness, I
don't like spiders,
what can I say?
How does "Sorry I got
you killed" sound?
Who are you?
Come on out!
Guess I'll have
to give myself up.
(audible sigh)
You stay here and
don't make a sound.
Huh?
♪
So, just what the hell
is your name anyway?
I'm Misao Makimachi,
but I don't give
just anybody my name.
Just try to find
out who I am.
Huh?
Uh, she just told
us her name, right?
Smart, she ain't.
I'm so embarrassed, oh.
How could I do that?
I don't care,
I really don't.
Now, all of you,
out of my way!
I said, "Back off,
or you're gonna get hurt!"
Is this some
kind of joke?
She just must be a fool.
Men, take her out!
(shouting)
The joke's on you, sucker!
So who's the fool now?
(grunting)
♪
Ah.
(smacking)
Ha, some punch line, huh?
Stop it!
Huh?
Eiji?
Oh.
You're gonna
be our guide.
Sneak us inside or
you're dead meat, get it?
But you're just a kid.
I'll bet that you've
never killed anybody,
and I'll bet you you
can't kill me either.
That's it, you're history.
Wait!
Take us inside
right now or you die.
Just calm down, kid.
I promise to do whatever
you say, all right?
(yelling)
(grunting)
♪
Keep running, you
little cockroach!
You can't keep
running forever,
I'll catch you
sooner or later,
and when I do, I'll
slice you into confetti!
(yelling)
Well, now.
Looks like Mr. Himura's
getting pushed to his limit
and he's not pushing back.
Aren't you going
to help him out?
No way, I wouldn't want
to show him all my tricks,
and besides, I don't think
he'd appreciate the help.
You'll see.
♪
Shishio looked a
hell of a lot happier
before this fight started.
He looks a lot
more serious now.
He's trying to understand
Kenshin's technique,
but he hasn't
quite got it yet.
But he'll understand
soon enough.
(grunting)
See how Shishio
watches him?
And Kenshin knows that his
strengths and weaknesses
are being assessed,
and that's why he's chosen
the self-destruct defense.
It gives away nothing.
Self-destruct?
It should be soon.
All right, that's it!
(grunting)
(screaming)
♪
(gasping)
(groaning)
It's--it's my leg,
I can't move it, ahh!
Ahh!
Moving that quickly for that
long pushed the thigh muscle
into a state of hypertension
which overloaded the
bone until it broke,
that's what caused
you to self-destruct.
Nonsense, we were both moving
at about the same speed!
My physique is perfect,
there's no way I could've
pushed my body beyond
its limits just
by chasing you.
You're muscular, all right.
You're so overdeveloped
that when you used
your full strength,
your bones couldn't
handle the overload.
No, no way!
Nothing like this has
ever happened to me before.
It can't be!
It must be a trick.
Tell me, how the hell
did you do this to me?
You still don't
get it, do you?
It's a trick, right?
Well, some might
call it that.
Actually, you tricked
yourself by following
Mr. Himura so closely.
He sped up every time
he got behind you
and you sped up with him.
And he kept making you
turn the same way each time.
The turning did it.
How?
You used the same leg
to turn with every time
until the bone couldn't
take it and self-destructed.
Ah.
These new fighting techniques
are really quite fascinating.
Huh?
♪
I haven't really
killed 99 men.
That was all
a lie, honest.
I've only killed
about a dozen men
and no women at all.
But you were the one
who killed my friend's
family, that right?
Eiji's family, I mean.
(gasping)
Senkaku!
Huh?
♪
I knew from the
very beginning
that you wouldn't be able
to beat Kenshin Himura.
But if you lose
without forcing him
to show me some
of his techniques,
I'm afraid I'll have
to kill you myself.
It won't be pleasant.
(grunting)
♪
-Through there?
-Yeah.
-No, ahh!
-Thank you!
Careful, Eiji,
we've got to
be super quiet.
♪
(gasping)
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
(speaking foreign language)
(grunting)
(yelling)
(thudding)
(gasping)
Do you see that?
Nice move.
Amazing.
(gasping)
Why did you
leave him alive?
He would've killed
you if he could have.
Someday showing mercy
is gonna get you killed.
I don't kill in cold
blood for any reason.
It doesn't serve
any purpose.
True.
But it can be amusing.
♪
Shishio.
Pick up your sword.
♪
The time has come.
(theme music)
♪