(theme song)
♪
Mr. Saeke's been
conning people.
I am completely
aware of all that.
Oh?
But there's more to it.
I'm sure this man
has much bigger plans.
He's putting in a railroad,
but it's not what
it seems to be.
He's building a tunnel instead.
♪
I am the head of
the water family.
We want our ki back,
and nothing will stop us!
(laughing)
(grunting)
Enough!
(snickers)
(grunting)
He's mine!
Take this!
Stop!
♪
No!
(screams)
(grunting)
Huh?
Kori!
She's dying.
(grunts)
♪
It is time now.
Time for war.
(thunder)
♪
(labored breathing)
Look at that.
(murmur of conversation)
♪
Kori's leg looks bad.
It is bad.
Huh?
Reisui used
a Tang feng shui method
that he learned in China.
It causes her wounds
to absorb poisonous air
which will make her body rot.
It's a death that's terrible.
I've heard about this,
but because this method
has been banned in Japan,
I've never had the chance
to observe something like this.
I don't understand it.
Why would anyone
want to be that cruel?
Mr. Jinpu, can Kori be cured?
Yes.
The spring at Musashino.
You're kidding me,
the same one?
Right.
Saeke's trying to build
that tunnel of his
to get that spring water.
It's very powerful.
The spring has been
filled with strong ki
ever since ancient times.
If used incorrectly,
it can be dangerous.
Saeke wants to exploit the ki
and use it for evil purposes.
We need that water.
It's the only way
to save her.
Mr. Jinpu, we have
to move quickly.
Help me find the way
to the spring water.
It's very important
we get to that spring
before it's too late for her.
-Let's go!
-No!
Huh?
Your job is to stay
here and protect Kori.
It could be
dangerous over there.
He's right.
Huh?
It's better that way.
She shouldn't be alone.
♪
Mm.
We should leave now.
I want to get the
troops ready to move.
Right.
Good luck, men.
We hope that you will succeed.
♪
Chief, tell Kawaji
to order his men
to find Saeke and lock him up.
We need some hard evidence.
Yes, sir.
This is the police!
I'll try upstairs, sir!
Look!
What a mess.
There's nothin' here, sir.
Not a soul, sir!
Sir, they must have known
that we were coming.
That is becoming rather obvious.
Huh?
We have to bring in Saeke
no matter what the cost,
even if we have to
bring in reinforcements.
Yes, sir!
Saeke doesn't need
this dojo anymore.
He has bigger fish to fry.
I doubt that there's
any danger of attack,
so I need you two to do
something while we're gone.
What do you mean?
Just this.
Saeke wants to destroy
our jin completely,
and he's building
up his own now.
I don't know how much
jin he has in place,
but I need you to look
for every one of
his centers of power.
And destroy them?
Is there some kind of sign
we should be looking for?
There should be
a symbol on each spot
that takes the form of a demon.
It represents
the Yurakimon Gate.
Mm-hm.
We're gonna be
counting on you two.
(labored breathing)
Hm, Jinpu.
His name sounds similar
to that of the wind family.
Could it be?
Hm.
He must be one of the last
of them alive on Earth.
If he is, then it's
going to be a problem.
Dammit.
We didn't plan on one of our
enemies getting in the way.
But don't worry,
we're sure to get rid of him
without any trouble.
Terrific.
I'm counting on you, my friend.
Come here.
♪
This is my plan,
so listen carefully.
We've destroyed
most of their jin,
but a few key targets remain.
We destroyed
the Ministry of Construction
using the energy that we
acquired from the restaurant
and the Kamiya dojo.
It's imperative that we
completely obliterate their jin.
To accomplish this goal,
we must manipulate the ki
to the northeastern
section of Musashino.
But before we do that,
we have to liberate the flow
from several strategic points.
Our next objective is to
destroy the Judicial Ministry
and the police department.
Ten Ruin is the final target.
That's what we decided, right?
That's right.
The building itself
is situated
on an important power point
in Tokugawa's
original jin formation.
He had deliberately designed
it to protect the city.
A cabinet meeting will be
held next week at that site.
High ranking officials
are scheduled to be there.
If we destroy it, we'll get
rid of all of them at once.
Then, the obliteration of
Tokugawa's jin will be complete,
and we can start our takeover.
We'll be in perfect position.
The destruction of Iguno jin
and the opportunity
to build a new formation
is our only goal.
Once we bump off
all those officials,
we'll be able to
take over the country.
It's all very simple.
So you're absolutely positive
that those officials
will be there?
I'm sure; I've got these
politicians under my thumb.
They've all been
handsomely paid off,
so it shouldn't be a problem.
(laughs)
It's going to be
well worth the money
to watch them all die.
That stupid Meiji government.
How do they expect to change
when they're still relying
on the jin of the past?
The building is on
a main point of jin.
That's a mistake.
It would eventually
destroy them anyway.
Oh well, I guess we'll just have
to speed up the process a bit.
They'll find out
how scary we are.
That will make it much more fun.
(evil laughter)
♪
(chanting)
(grunting)
(thunder)
(screaming)
(grunting)
♪
(indistinct conversation)
It's a demon.
Which means that
it's a point of jin.
We have to get
over there and stop it.
Heh, I don't exactly
specialize in manual labor,
but I'll try.
Out of my way, move!
I've got some jin to crush.
♪
Just as I expected!
(grunting)
♪
Huh.
Is he a man or a monkey?
♪
Oh...
Oh, I can't believe it.
The police department
is completely demolished.
This makes no sense at all.
Hm--huh?
Stop your moaning, Chief.
I'm telling you, knock it off!
Huh?
You get up from there.
But, sir, can't you see
the police department's
been destroyed!
There's nothing
left but some rubble.
Stupid, I'm not blind,
I can see that!
So what happened with
your investigation?
We don't know.
So far, nobody in his company's
been able to tell us
where Mr. Saeke is, sir.
Well, step up your
efforts and find that guy.
All other investigations
are to be put on hold.
Let's get that bastard.
A spring of ki is actually
flowing beneath the ground?
It's hard to believe there
is such a thing in Kanto.
Tokugawa was extremely fortunate
to base his
headquarters here in Edo.
This land is literally flowing
with a positive ki force.
If you think about it,
that's one of the main reasons
the Tokugawa Era lasted
for well over 300 years.
Hm.
♪
Tell me, Jinpu,
do you think it's possible
Reisui intentionally hurt Kori
so they could lure us
to Musashino and trap us?
♪
Although it doesn't really
matter if they did or not.
I'll do anything
I can to save her life.
Listen to me.
When Commander Perry came,
I was married to a woman.
One day I woke up and
found out she'd left me.
She was unhappy with the fact
that I was so
dedicated to feng shui.
I was never able to have
children because of it,
so there's no one
to carry on my name.
Ever since I met you, I felt
as though you were like me,
but I guess you're not.
I was too immersed
in my vocation
and didn't realize
I was losing her.
(sighs)
So Kenshin,
I made a big mistake,
and I can't make up
for my mistakes,
but you still have the
chance to do what's right.
Sorry, Jinpu.
You really must
cherish her, Kenshin.
If you're constantly obsessed
with what you're doing,
you'll become like me,
and you don't want to be.
The days of the
sword toting samurai
ended with the Tokugawa Era.
Feng shui will end as well.
We have to learn to
put the past behind us
and look forward to the future.
It'll make us happier.
Well, sir, ever
since the destruction
of the Ministry of Construction,
the judiciary,
and the police department,
swarms of people
have left the city.
So far, we have been
unable to secure the area
and prevent any more
damage to public buildings.
We need more manpower.
What?
Deploy all battalions.
I want each and
every one of them
assembled and prepared to march.
Every one of them?
But that's a lot of men.
We have no choice.
I want them to
head for Musashino
and destroy Saeke's
railroad construction area.
He has got to be stopped.
By the way,
I'll be leading the attack,
so let's get going.
♪
(grunting)
Ah...
Those men never stop.
Tsunan told me he's got
men working double shifts.
We can't avoid them.
We can't afford to wait.
There just isn't
much time left.
Yes, you're right.
I'm afraid we'll just
have to take a chance.
Are you ready?
Sure, let's go.
♪
(panting)
(shouting)
(screaming)
♪
I'll take care of this.
Jin, go back!
(grunting)
Let's go!
♪
I'm here from
the police department.
I need to see
Yamagata right away.
Well, he's out of
his office right now.
Perhaps I could help you?
What's the matter, sir?
Our building has
gone up in smoke,
so we need you to
give us some space.
Uh, that's impossible.
We have no extra space here.
Then make some,
and hurry it up!
Follow me, men!
(maniacal laughter)
So where's that spring?
Keep running,
it's in the back.
Jin!
(speaking foreign language)
(screaming)
(creaking)
Huh?
♪
Oh no.
What was that?
They must have put a special
kind of jin in this tunnel
to keep us from trespassing.
It reacts to my technique
and then it retaliates
automatically.
It acts like a mirror.
Well, how are we gonna
stop it from doing that?
I have a plan.
We'll get there,
don't you worry.
♪
There's another one.
It's got the face of a demon.
Hey, they know we're here
and they're after us.
Be careful, Sanosuke.
(grunting)
(maniacal laughter)
Go for it!
♪
Thanks, pal!
(grunting)
♪
When will we get
to the spring, Jinpu?
We should be there soon.
♪
It keeps going.
I know.
But we can't stop now.
(panting)
Huh?
♪
It's all blocked.
We've come to a dead end.
How are we gonna
find the spring?
That five point
star is being used
to protect the spring
against enemies.
The spring is
probably behind it.
Hm.
Hm?
The power of the ki
is very strong.
It may have the
potential to be dangerous.
He has purposely directed
the energy flow to the spring,
making the ki capable
of doing damage.
I just hope I'm wrong.
Saeke must be planning
a major attack
as a means to take
over the government.
Mm-hm.
I'm sure.
Wait.
This doesn't make
much sense to me.
It's quite a distance
between here and the city.
The power will decrease
by the time it gets there.
Still, we can't take a chance
of letting something
that disastrous happen.
It's monstrous.
♪
So what do you plan to do now?
Just one thing.
What?
Destroy the star.
I thought you said
your feng shui technique
doesn't work
inside this tunnel.
If we want to obtain the water,
we must try,
so move out of the way
and get ready for anything.
What do you want me to do?
You keep the jin men away.
♪
Right, ready.
(chanting)
♪
(gasps)
(screaming)
(grunting)
♪
You must be in pain.
(screaming)
(maniacal laughter)
Looks like there's more of them.
Huh?
Watch out!
♪
(commotion)
(screaming)
Oh!
What's that?
This is bad.
The ki is beginning to flow
in a spiral pattern
against the wall.
Ki energy is only
beneficial to the world
if it flows in a straight line.
When it does,
it's peaceful and harmonious,
but once it starts to spiral,
the speed increases and
it becomes too powerful.
Then it becomes unpredictable.
The violence it creates
cannot be tamed.
This mighty force
can turn into an evil
weapon of destruction.
But, Jinpu, this is big trouble.
What if the ki spirals
from Musashino to the city?
Ah?
Huh?
(growling)
Looks like those pests
want a little more.
I think I know how
to get rid of them,
but I'll have to use
chizumi no jin,
so stand back.
It could hurt you.
♪
It's much too strong.
Yes, but if I put
my body into it,
then it will calm
down the ki flow.
That may be able to stop it.
(shrieking)
(grunting)
(shouting chant)
Take my energy and settle down.
♪
Feel my positive energy
calling to you and be still!
Huh?
Oh!
Oh...
(soft otherworldly sounds)
Calm your spiraling flow.
Don't be persuaded by the water
family's plan of corruption.
Stay on the course
of harmony and peace.
(soft otherworldly sounds)
Oh no!
A crack.
The force of the flow
is just too powerful.
(cracking)
What's gonna happen now?
It's coming!
Ah!
The tunnel's not
able to support it.
We have to get out.
You can do it!
Take the water.
Come on!
Ah...
Enough.
We have to save the rest
to help Kori get better.
I hope you're right about that.
Sir, sir!
Good news!
I found them, they both made
it out of there and survived.
They look ragged
but they're all right.
♪
We have to get back.
We'll make sure that you do,
so don't worry about it.
Has the problem been solved?
No, in fact,
it's more serious
that we thought it was.
Just what do you mean?
The tunnel's gone,
but the ki has been
released to the northeast.
Yes, our work at Musashino
has been successful,
and those two idiots
just saved us the trouble
of doing it ourselves.
Well, we'll need to make certain
they don't bother us again.
Usui, I will make
the journey north
and follow the ki's path.
You stay here and
take care of the city.
Yes, that's the plan
I had in mind.
The ki has started to
move at a rapid pace.
No one is capable
of stopping it now.
♪
What's that?
Are you trying to tell me
we have absolutely no control?
Because the ki's spiraling,
it'll be hard to aim it
into the right spot.
They need to develop a
strategy to harness it.
We have to outmaneuver
their jin to beat them.
That means we'll have to
follow the path of the ki.
Which direction is it
heading right now?
It's heading northeast
right into the next town,
the town of Nikko.
♪
Nikko.
(theme song)
♪