♪
I can't stand the suspense.
Who do you think
will win, Shishio?
It's hard to say.
Kenshin and Aoshi
are too evenly matched.
What if they both
strike each other
and fall down
at the same time?
Then our job
would be done.
I'm hoping that Kenshin will
beat the pants off of him,
and then, maybe I'll
finally get my chance
to get back at him
for what he did.
But Aoshi is
a strong fighter.
What are you
planning to do
if he turns out
to be the winner?
That's easy.
I'll crush him
like an insect.
(snickers)
Aoshi will be defeated then
I'll be the most powerful.
He'll never
know what hit him.
♪
What are you trying
to tell me, Kenshin?
You heard me
loud and clear.
And that's the reason
I refuse to fight you.
How would you know
enough about me
to come to that
insane conclusion?
My mind is weak?
That's right.
Beshimi.
Hyottoko.
Shikijo.
Han'nya.
You aren't going to do
any of them justice
simply by beating me!
The best way you
can honor them
is by making peace
with yourself.
Don't use them to absolve your
guilt by weakening your mind.
Because if you're not careful,
it will destroy you.
♪
Why don't you shut up?
Now...
die!
(grunts)
You know that I'm
telling you the truth.
You must be in a
state of denial,
but I believe that you
know it in your heart.
Not true.
(groans)
♪
You know nothing.
You must listen to me.
You've lost touch
with reality
and your selfishness has
gotten the better of you.
Until you accept this Aoshi,
you will never be able to earn
the title of most powerful.
Shut up.
(groaning)
Go ahead and dig
your own grave, Aoshi.
Until you erase those
thoughts from your brain,
you will forever be
anguished by the guilt
of letting those
four men die.
I said shut up.
(grunting)
You have a chance, but now,
no matter what you do--
(grunts)
Those men's souls will never
be able to rest in peace.
♪
It seems to be working.
I can imagine that
it must be humiliating
to be taunted by someone who
is more powerful than yourself,
and to have to tell
that person the truth.
Face to face.
Not as an enemy,
but as a person.
This confrontation
has to be more painful
than being struck by a sword.
Aoshi, because of
your shortcomings,
you feel the weight
of blame and dishonor
for all of their deaths,
and that will cause them
to be tormented souls.
♪
Those men deserve
justice by the sword.
♪
Huh?
Aoshi, I don't know if you
happened to hear the news.
Misao has unofficially
declared herself
the leader of the Oni gang.
She's using that position
to help the people of Edo stay
safe from the Juupongatana.
Hmm, Misao is
a strong woman.
And she certainly
could handle it.
But I don't think it's
a good idea for her
to become the leader
of the Oni gang.
She's certainly capable, but--
There's something
else about Misao.
She became very
upset when I told her
I was going to
bring you back.
She shed tears.
Did you know that Aoshi?
No matter how incredibly
strong she seems to be,
she's only a
young girl of 18.
The harsh reality she faces
forces her to take on
the responsibilities
of someone twice her age.
And you, Aoshi,
are the only person
that she will
honestly respond to,
so come to your senses.
Get your pride back.
It's time to forget about
what happened in the past.
Open your eyes!
You can't undo what's
already been done.
If you don't listen, then
you'll destroy yourself.
Stop this fixation
with being so powerful,
or it'll turn you
into a mad man.
Are you listening to
what I have to say?
(gunfire)
(groans)
It's your decision, Aoshi.
What's it going to be?
(grunts)
Aoshi?
I...
I must finish this fight.
It's a point of honor.
You understand,
Kenshin, don't you?
It's the only way
I'll be able to go on
living with myself.
I understand how
you feel, Aoshi.
And I'm willing to
continue with the fight.
♪
I wouldn't do it, Kenshin.
His eyes are looking
different than they usually do.
I know.
Don't think I haven't
noticed it too.
This isn't the
Aoshi Shinomori
that became involved
with Takata.
This is the man
that Okina nurtured,
those four men respected
and Misao loved.
He reminds me of the
old Aoshi from years ago.
There's something about
him I can't explain.
It makes no difference
whether we win or lose.
I agree with you.
I hope that this will
be our last battle ever.
We'll give it
everything that we have.
I've got to
give this my all.
♪
This match promises
to be very exciting.
But who will make
the first move?
Their level of
concentration is so astounding
that it's hard to tell.
But I'm willing
to bet that Aoshi
will be the first to attack.
He's by far the most
aggressive of the two.
Kenshin's been cut on
both sides of his neck.
If Aoshi begins the
circling sword dance,
one false move or
mishap on Kenshin's part
could prove to be fatal.
Kenshin won't
initiate an attack.
He's conserving
his energy.
This will put him
in the perfect position
to use the secret principle
if he finds that he needs to.
I don't think Aoshi will jump
in just to get things started.
It's strictly gamesmanship now.
This leaves
things pretty equal.
Neither one of them wants to be
the first one to make a mistake.
♪
Beshimi.
Hyottoko.
Shikijo.
Han'nya.
Please, you must forgive me.
I've been lying to myself.
The truth is that
I was using your deaths
as an excuse
for my own problems.
I wasn't seeing clearly.
But that's going to end soon.
I'm dedicating this
battle to you.
And whether I win or lose,
I hope to honor you.
♪
Damn.
I can hardly breathe.
It's probably
only been ten minutes
but it feels much longer.
They still haven't
budged an inch.
You can cut the tension
in this room with a knife.
One of them will
have to give in
and make the first move,
but who will it be?
(gasps)
I hear something.
But where's it coming from?
(telegraph clicking)
Oh, Ayumi!
♪
Hmm.
No, hold it!
She's telegraphing the battle,
and sending it to Shishio.
Don't give
the move away!
No, hold it!
She's telegraphing the battle
and sending it to Shishio.
Don't give
the move away!
(grunts)
Kaiten Kenbu Rokuren.
♪
You must live, Kenshin.
Then you will be able to use
the secret principle freely,
and never lose the spirit
of the slasher within you.
Remember, you must live.
It's not just
Megumi and myself.
Everybody is praying
that you will come
back safe and sound.
I understand now.
My mind is clear and there's
nothing to be afraid of.
And I am ready.
Hiten-mitsurugi.
♪
(grunts)
(groans)
♪
(moans)
(gasps)
(machine clicking)
Master Shishio.
We just got a telegraph
message from Ayumi.
She says that Himura
has used his trump card.
Apparently she says,
his secret principle
is performed
by using a Battu sword
pulling maneuver.
The only problem is Ayumi
was unable to see it.
Damn.
(chuckles)
That Ayumi is
just useless.
(laughing)
Ayumi makes me laugh.
Quiet down,
you bumbling idiot.
It appears that
Ayumi has given us
some important information that
may be quite helpful to us.
It seems Kenshin's
secret is a variation
of the Battu technique and
he was able to pull it off
in spite of Aoshi's
kaiten kenbu.
Huh?
I can't comprehend the power
of the secret principle.
It must have a
hidden characteristic
that makes it so unique,
but what the hell is it?
(metal scraping)
(breathing heavily)
♪
Aoshi?
You came very close
to beating me.
♪
Maybe so, but not
close enough I'm afraid.
You beat me.
I accept that
you defeated me.
♪
I'm sorry I
had to hurt you.
Can you stand up?
Not for a while.
My body's completely numb,
but I feel better.
It's like a giant weight
was taken off my shoulders.
Kenshin, that last
maneuver of yours.
Tell me about it.
You must tell me just
where it came from.
Please.
I'd be honored to share
it with you, my friend.
It's one of the
secret principles
of the hiten-mitsurugi style.
Its power is beyond
anything I've ever seen.
It doesn't surprise me
that this technique's
been kept a
secret for so long.
Kenshin?
You should keep
this move under wraps.
Exerting that much power
will eventually take its toll
on your body's stamina.
And even though it's an
extraordinary technique,
its impact will probably
be reduced by half
once the enemy is able to
get a hold of its details.
Thank you.
That's good advice.
I thank you
for it, Aoshi.
Won't be needing
that anymore.
Allow me to
telegraph my feelings.
I feel better.
So what?
It's already too late.
Kenshin!
Ayumi has already
spilled the beans.
We gotta get
out of here.
(Ayumi grunting)
You'd better go.
I'll follow
in a while.
I'll be all right.
Get your hands off of me,
you stupid brute.
Just quit
your complaining.
♪
Tell me, which way
do we get out of here?
Right now!
I'm not going to
tell you anything
until you let go,
you big moron!
Alright, which way is it?
Left or right?
We came from the left.
What do you think, of course,
it's the right, you freak!
"Freak?"
Who are you
calling a freak?
Beshimi.
Old Hyottoko.
Shikijo.
Han'nya.
I'm sorry to cause
you so much pain.
I just wasn't
strong enough
to deserve the title
of most powerful,
but I have fought
with everything I had,
and I have no regrets.
That man has honored
his promise to me.
I must return the favor
and go back to the others.
If...
I'm forgiven
for all I've done.
Especially for attempting
to murder good Okina.
♪
I'm so strong and powerful,
I can't stand it.
(chuckling)
Not one of you will
be able to get by me.
So, what do you say?
One of you wanna try it?
(gasps)
Misao!
Mustn't leave
your position.
If we stay put, they
won't get the upper hand.
Everybody get up
and hold your ground.
We're not going to let
those bastards beat us.
If we can hang on
just a little bit longer,
the police will
come and help us.
Don't worry, Okina!
We won't back down!
Oh, give me a break.
You expect the
police to come?
That's a big joke.
Fire!
Fire in the city!
♪
(laughing evilly)
(shudders)
Help me,
help me.
It's a monster!
(yelling)
(laughing)
This is child's play.
They're running away
like scared mice.
This'll keep them busy.
Fuji, I believe it's time
for me to now go to Aoiya.
(growls)
Alright, what's the
big hold up, huh?
Could we hurry up and
get on with this please?
Why don't we start?
I'm getting really
tired of this stance.
Just hold your
horses, Kamatari!
I'm ready to take
her on, right now
and I bet that
I can beat her.
We're not going to be able
to go back and join the others
until we get this
old bag out of the way,
and all you have to do
is give me the chance.
Would you calm down, Misao?
Don't go sticking
your neck out
with that big sickle
she's carrying around.
That bimbo could wipe you
off the face of the Earth.
She's not exactly
an ordinary woman.
(snickers)
Well, I think you're
definitely right about that.
You're very perceptive
for a little boy.
Hey, who you
calling a boy?
I'm sorry to insult you.
It's just you're such
a cute lad, that's all,
and you do have
some potential.
"Potential?"
Oh, come on.
You're not about
to seduce me
with your smoldering
red-hot sex appeal,
even though you
really are a fox!
It really doesn't
matter to me
that you're sexier
than Misao or Kaoru.
Hey, what are you talking
about, you dim little twerp?
Yeah, Yoshi, I can
understand about Misao
because she's not
that attractive,
but there's no way that
Kamatari is sexier than me.
What are you
talking about, Kaoru?
You're supposed
to be on my side.
Oh, right,
I'm sorry.
Yoshi,
we demand an apology.
What?
But it's true.
Oh, Yoshi,
you're an idiot.
What do you see in that
tall drink of water anyway?
She may not be ugly but
she's probably cold as ice.
It's not worth it, Misao.
He wouldn't
know a real woman
if she were staring
at him in the face.
Those women must be really
desperate, poor things.
They need to find
themselves a boyfriend
before they both dry up.
I think you could
be really something
if you had the
right training.
So, how about it kid?
You'd be really smart
to join up with me.
What training?
Yeah, just what
are you talking about?
I don't want any part
of your stupid training
if it makes a
man into a woman.
Huh?
Oh, yeah?
You don't really
think that's true.
Ooh.
-Kamatari is a man?
(groaning)
I lost to a guy?
Right, in your
dreams, Misao.
I'm the real thing.
You'll never be
half the woman I am.
Even if I choose
to let you survive,
so why don't you accept the
truth and forget about it?
Why you-- oh!
Come on, Misao, cool out.
If you keep this up,
we're gonna fall
right into their trap.
Kaoru, please.
Stop your squawking
and let's figure out
what to do about this.
Misao can't take on this
responsibility alone.
Well, do you
have a better idea?
You're way too inexperienced
to fight by yourself,
so our only other
option is Misao.
You trained me to be a man
that can handle
anything on his own,
and I'm determined
to show you that I can.
It's time you trusted
your top student, Kaoru.
♪
I wouldn't mind seeing that
young stud strut his stuff.
Why don't you give
him his big chance?
Then you can see if
he's a man or just a wimp.
Mm-hmm.
We may have
no other choice.
I believe we'd
better do what Yoshi says.
♪
Hmm, it's against
my better judgment,
but we'll have
to trust you.
I had hoped we could
complete your training
before sending
you out by yourself.
There are still more Kamiya
Kasshin style techniques
that you haven't
mastered yet.
I'm just afraid that
you may have some trouble.
I can do it.
Alright, but we'd better
stay here and back him up.
You got it.
You just go ahead and try.
I'll make chop suey
out of both of you.
♪
They're pitting me
against Henya.
He looks like a
tricky character.
(growls)
Don't look so bored.
You have no idea
who you're fighting.
Come on and try it,
you big loser.
You'll have to excuse me,
but I'm somewhat disappointed.
It's just that
I was not expecting
to match wills
with a mere boy.
I've heard so much
about this Hiten-mitsurugi
style of yours,
and I have to admit,
it intrigues me.
So much so, that in fact,
I've become obsessed
with fighting against it.
But then, Shishio
sends me here
and now I find myself
fighting an ordinary kid.
It's ridiculous.
What a waste of time.
I'm not an ordinary kid,
and I'm gonna prove
it to you, Hen-house.
Hmm?
Alright, now
listen to me.
I've witnessed many of
Kenshin Himura's battles
and I think
I'm very capable.
Watching those battles
have taught me more
than anything else.
I know all his moves.
Backwards and forwards.
Nobody has studied his
technique as much as I have.
Why do you turn
your back on me, Henya?
(clucking)
Are you chicken?
Let me tell you,
you wanna fight with Kenshin,
then you'd better
start with me.
Alright, boy, if you're
so bent on dying young,
then let's get on with it.
I'm not going to
kill you slowly.
First, I'll
make you regret
that you ever tried
to ridicule me, boy.
Now, get ready to suffer.
Keep an eye on
this wingding,
he's got something
in his hands.
It looks like
some kind of bomb.
I thought he had more
imagination than that.
Too bad.
I thought you
were a real warrior,
but you're just
a phony and a coward,
and you were bragging
about how good you were.
What a big liar!
I never said I was going
to kill you in
just one blast, boy.
This is for fun.
(shouts)
This is my own
battle technique.
(laughing)
I'm the winged warrior
of the Juupongatana.
It's flying
blaster time.
(gasping)
No matter what technique
a person has mastered,
he can't beat someone
that he can't touch.
You're a sitting duck, kid.
You dare humiliate me?
Now, you're going to regret
that and die, you fool.
(shouting)
Yoshi!