♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪
Guess it's time to say goodbye.
Kaoru, when you get to Edo
please go visit Sherry Baby's.
That's my old restaurant.
I've already written
to let them know you're coming.
Okay, Sherry Baby's.
Thank you, thanks a lot.
You know, that's the
sister restaurant of Lenny's.
I feel so lonely.
It seems like everyone
is leaving Kyoto.
Bye, Yoshi.
Take care of yourself.
Sure.
We won't be gone very long.
We'll find him.
And be back real soon.
-Bye.
-See ya.
When you come back
I'll make you some sashimi.
Yeah!
Kaoru, wait!
Huh?
Don't go yet!
We made it, we made it!
Hi, everybody!
You got here just in time.
Take care now.
I'm really gonna miss you all.
Well, I'm glad
to see the patient
is finally well
enough to travel.
Good luck, Kaoru!
So long, Kaoru!
Say hi to all the ladies
in Edo for me.
Thank you again
for all your help!
Huh?
If it weren't for you
and all the support
and encouragement you gave me
I don't know what I would have--
Well, I'm glad you
finally realized
all the appreciation I deserve.
Now get going, you silly fool,
before that riverboat
leaves without you.
Now don't forget to write!
And be sure to
give our best wishes
to our friend Kenshin
when you find him.
Bon voyage!
So long!
Be safe!
And don't forget to write!
Come back soon, okay?
Goodbye!
♪
All right, Yoshi,
now our mission
is to go find Kenshin.
That's right.
♪
(crash)
Yah!
♪
I'll get stronger.
So strong that Kenshin will know
that I should have
gone along with him.
♪
I'm not your weakness, Kenshin.
You'll see.
And I shall prove
it to you in Edo.
You hear me, Kenshin?
In Edo!
(sneezes)
Strange.
I never thought that I
would walk this road again.
Look, Mom, a sword.
Sh, be quiet.
He looks like a samurai.
What's with him?
Do you think he doesn't know
about the new decree
banning the wearing
of swords in public?
He looks dangerous to me.
The best thing to do
is to stay away from him.
♪
Did you say goodbye to that girl
at Kamiya Dojo?
Sorry, I shouldn't
have said that.
From now on we're
fellow warriors
who are going to fight
the Shishio Group together,
so let's make the best of it.
Fight together?
Yes.
You see, since the
Okubo assassination
the police are facing
some serious problems.
Therefore I was assigned to
handle the situation in Edo.
I get the feeling
you don't like the idea
of joining forces, Kenshin.
Not really.
I understand that.
But you'll have to anyway,
like it or not.
Come on.
If we leave now we can
catch the ship for Osaka.
Nope, I'm going to
take the Tokaido Road.
Hm?
The government will
pay for your ticket
so if you're broke just
don't worry about it.
It's not about the money.
Shishio is crafty like a fox.
If he arranges an attack
while I'm on the ship
there'd be no place to fight
where innocent people
wouldn't be put in danger.
I can't allow that to happen.
You still think like a wanderer
living in a world that exists
only in your dreams.
Perhaps it's time
for me to wake you up.
I would be glad to fight
you any time you like, Saito.
But I have no intention
of letting anyone
who isn't involved
in this get hurt.
That's why I'm taking
this journey alone.
♪
Aren't you forgetting something?
Like what?
Shishio's spies.
He's got a very efficient
information network.
And he'll know
exactly where you are
no matter what route you take.
♪
Like it or not your battle
with Shishio's already begun.
All I have to do is
have a sword at my side
and people will
stay away from me.
That way I won't
have to involve anyone.
Makoto Shishio was
responsible for Okubo's death.
That's why I must go to Edo,
to stop Shishio's
reign of terror.
I wonder what awaits me
at the end of my journey.
(whistle)
Hold it now.
You've got some
nerve wearing a sword
in front of an officer
of the law, young man.
Stop!
Hold it right
there, you villain!
I'm out of here.
Stop, stop in the
name of the law!
♪
It's so lonely here now
that everyone's gone.
I'll take good care of
things while they're away.
Hm, should be locked.
It's open.
But I have the only key.
Unless...
Kenshin!
He's come back!
Kenshin?
♪
Aoshi, you?
I want you to tell
me where Battosai is.
Unbelievable.
But we all thought
you were dead.
But after all this time
you must have escaped.
That's right.
Even if I knew where he was
I would never ever tell you.
You tell me now.
Or die.
♪
He's on his way to Edo.
And just who the hell are you?
Goro Fujita, a policeman,
and I'm working undercover.
No, your name's Saito.
You're a former head of the
Shinsen Group, third division.
You're an expert at gotatsu.
Now it looks like you're
just a government lackey.
I see.
It seems to me your Oni
Gang's information is accurate
as usual.
The reason I came here
was because I heard
that another survivor
of the end of the Tokugawa
era had come to Tokyo.
I wanted to tell
you what's happened
since you secluded
yourself on that mountain.
♪
Makoto Shishio.
Let's say Battosai
is killed by Shishio.
That he isn't coming back.
In that case, tell me,
how would you like to go to Edo?
I don't need to.
I'm the only one that can do
battle with Battosai and win.
You have a great
deal of confidence.
The question to me is whether
or not it's overconfidence.
How could you give
him that information?
He wants to kill Kenshin!
Now that he knows
where Kenshin is headed
he'll know the
routes he might take.
He'll know where to
look, and if he finds--
Look on the bright side.
If I hadn't have told him that
he might very well
have killed you.
Aoshi Shinomori became
head of the Oni Gang
at the age of 15.
If I can find a way to use him
it'll give us a
tremendous advantage.
I like the way your
mind works, policeman.
Yeah, Saito, I agree.
Aoshi Shinomori.
Could be quite useful indeed.
Would you stop already?
Come back here, you rascal!
You scofflaw!
I'm warning you, don't
get involved with me,
you could get hurt,
leave me alone.
Halt you cad,
halt at once, halt!
(crash)
Who am I kidding?
This isn't training.
It's merely destroying nature.
Where's the road to Edo?
Where is the road to Edo?
♪
I won't give up until
I destroy Battosai.
Only then can I bring flowers
to honor the graves
of my fallen comrades.
Give me that bottle of sake.
We gotta meet some girls.
Nah, you're too ugly.
Why, you, I oughtta...
You should talk!
Hey, look who's here.
Well, it's about time.
We've been waiting for you.
You're Aoshi Shinomori, right?
Yeah, he's Aoshi, all right.
Who are you?
And why are you here?
We're here for you.
We were sent here
by Mr. Shishio.
We're the Four
Giants of Abukuma.
And we're here to tell you
that Mr. Shishio
wants to see ya.
He's a great man
and doesn't have time
to just see anyone.
Even we rarely get to see him
and we work for him.
Going to meet him
is a great honor.
We better go now.
We don't wanna keep
him waiting, do we?
You can tell Shishio
if he wants to see me
he'll have to come to me.
And if you dare to desecrate
the graves of my comrades
you will all die.
Not only you,
but Shishio as well.
Ha, so much for
your dead buddies.
Threatening us
was stupid enough.
But threatening Mr.
Shishio was really idiotic.
Why do you say that?
(all)
Because now we gotta kill ya.
♪
A long sword.
You lost to Battosai
and changed your weapon.
It doesn't matter
how good you are.
You can't protect yourself
from all of us with one sword.
Huh?
One sheathe?
With two swords?
No way!
No!
It's so quick!
(thud)
(clapping)
That was truly amazing.
You didn't even give
the Abukuma Giants
time to use their specialty,
the four body unification move.
Kodachi double sword, very nice.
Who are you?
Do you work for Shishio?
Right.
My name is Sojiro Seta
and I am Mr. Shishio's
right hand man.
My goodness, I can see
why they call you a genius.
So, Aoshi.
Can't you just come and listen
to what we have to say?
Why should I?
Look, I don't plan on
working for anybody.
Especially not a guy who
throws away people's lives
like they were chess pieces
simply in order to judge
the strength of his opponent.
You knew what he
was doing all along.
But knowing they were
throwaway chess pieces
you killed them anyway.
So what?
You're different, right?
♪
Well, at any rate.
You were in the Oni Gang
during the Tokugawa era
and you defended Edo castle
at the end of the Tokugawa era.
But the story of how fiercely
you and your gang fought
was never told.
And then the
Tokugawa period ended.
And guess what?
You were just an unknown.
The reputation that you had
worked so hard to developed
had disappeared.
The Meiji government
has left no room
for you or your Oni
gang to operate.
Now your comrades
are either dead
or they've just given up.
But work for Shishio
and you'll restore
your reputation.
Boss, boss.
Boss.
We enjoyed our life,
that's why we chose it.
We lived and died
as the Oni Gang.
That's the truth.
We wouldn't lie.
I wish we could all relive
the end of the Tokugawa era
and fight by your
side again, boss.
That's how we all feel, Aoshi.
The reputation that you had
worked so hard to develop
has disappeared.
The Meiji government
has left no room
for you or your
Oni Gang to operate.
But if you work for Shishio
you'll restore your reputation.
To Edo.
Looks like those flowers
will just have to wait.
There's something I have
to take care of first.
♪
What do you think, Sir?
Do you like him?
Very much.
I like the way he
kills other people
as if they were garbage.
It might be difficult
getting him on our side.
You needn't worry about that.
Eventually I'll figure
out a way to use him.
Well, Sir, could you give me
something else to do, please?
Sojiro.
Perhaps it would be wise for you
to go and say hello
to a certain slasher.
Whatever do you mean?
Are you talking about
that Battosai guy?
Please excuse me.
Mr. Shishio.
I hope you're
having a good time.
Mmm, a very good time,
the fun has just begun.
What the hell?
I'm supposed to be
on a mountain road
but I find myself in this field.
Now what's going on?
Now wait a second,
if I can find out
where north is...
Aha.
Which means that
west is that way.
Then Edo is that way, too.
Sick five, I'm going to Edo!
I wonder if Kenshin is okay.
Huh?
The Shishio Group was
enough to deal with,
but now we have Aoshi
to deal with as well.
Ah!
What'll we do?
My hair!
Check her out!
Sure would like to
get to know her better.
Hi, guys.
Whoa, yeah!
Great food, right here!
Come stay at my inn
and you'll eat as
well as you ever have,
I promise you that!
Sorry, I'm in a hurry,
I'm going to visit
a sick friend.
But it'll be dark soon
and there's no moon.
You won't be able
to find your way.
If I spend the night here
Shishio's men might find me.
Hey, what's the
matter, you broke?
Got a place to stay tonight?
Don't bother, he's a deadbeat.
No money.
Oh boy, I should have known.
It's amazing how friendly
the people are here,
they talk to you even when
you're carrying a sword.
Huh?
It's been a long time
since I camped out.
It's kind of nice.
♪
I bet ya everyone is mad at me.
The way I left things
I wouldn't blame any
of them for hating me.
Huh?
(laughing)
They're too noisy to
be the Shishio Group,
maybe they're thieves.
Maybe if I stay
quiet they'll leave
and I'll go unnoticed.
What are you trying to do,
just tease us?
Yeah, why you so
shy all of a sudden?
You said we could, you know.
Well, actually you see,
I'm pretty new at this.
To tell you the truth I'm a,
I'm a virgin.
Yeah.
Yay, jackpot!
Use that sexy voice again.
Come on, let's get to
whammin' and slammin' huh?
Let's see what you got
under there, girly girl.
Oh, you will.
But first let me see the cash.
No problem, we just stole
this chunk of change yesterday
in Otawara.
Well, all right.
Come on.
So are you boys man enough?
Money!
I want everything you got,
hand it over now.
♪
But she's just a girl.
Let's go.
I thought she was
a full grown woman.
I'd do her.
Probably past her bedtime.
Hold it right
there, you dimwits!
♪
Call me a kid, will ya?
Nobody calls me that
and gets away with it.
I ain't no kid, I'm 18.
You gotta respect your elders.
And we teach the kind of respect
that you never forget.
I think a little pain
will help you remember.
Hold her down!
Huh?
♪
A little pain, that's
what you said, right?
I couldn't agree more!
Unbelievable, works every time.
All I've gotta do
is use my sexy voice
and they follow me like kids
who think they're
gonna get some candy.
Amazing.
Huh?
I kinda figured that somebody
was stealing from somebody,
but I didn't think the thief
was gonna turn out to be a girl.
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
I'm just a wanderer
walking in the woods.
So I'm a thief who
happens to be female,
what's wrong with that?
Hey, there's nothing wrong
with your being a female.
Nothing wrong with that.
What's wrong is you're a thief.
So, another man who thinks
he can tell a woman what to do.
I should take
everything you've got.
But you don't look like you've
got anything worth taking.
You look so...
Well, I don't mean to be rude,
but you don't have
a penny, do you?
Well, not exactly
♪
Well, friend,
if you have anything I'll
get it sooner or later.
No doubt about that.
Because one thing's for sure,
no man is a match for me.
♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪