♪
(singing in foreign language)
(fighting and groaning)
♪
Okay, I-I got it,
we got it,
we made a big mistake.
We shouldn't fight you,
you're just too
strong to handle.
Fine, I'm done.
I'm glad you figured things out.
What?
Somehow I thought
you four could test me.
(chuckles)
I guess I should've
known better.
♪
Where must I go to find
an opponent worth fighting?
♪
Not last night but
the night before...
(laughing)
...thirty-two ninjas
came knocking at my door.
Kori's a pretty good juggler.
Good juggler, Kori.
...I hit them
with a rolling pin.
Yeah, even ugly girl's
good for something else
besides kendo.
Hmm--ow!
Hey, Kori, what'd
you do that for?
I was just trying to
pay you a compliment!
I've got some news
for you, Yoshi.
With that kind of attitude,
girls will never want
to be around you.
Well, the way you act,
no guy would ever want to
get near you, raccoon face.
I've had it!
(blowing raspberry)
Come back here, you!
Well, I guess I'd better
start making lunch.
Kenshin, so what's on
your menu for lunch today?
Hmm...
Kohlrabi and duck foot soup.
Hey, wait!
I can also bring out my eggplant
that I've been pickling
underground for us.
I really hate eggplant.
I wish we had some money so
we could all go out to eat.
Because of our vegetable garden,
we always have a lot to eat,
but until we get
more dojo students,
we don't have enough money
to eat at a restaurant.
Boy, would it be great if
we had some paying students,
but the only thing we're
collecting at this dojo is dust.
Hey, outta my way!
(door creaking open)
There's some money in here!
Oh, brother, that
Kori's at it again!
Oh, no.
(laughing)
Oh, man, her brain got
warped by all that dust.
(laughing)
Here it is!
My great uncle left this to me.
Just what is it?
Don't you know about art?
It's a painting!
My, those certainly are
skilled brush strokes.
Is it an original
painting, Kori?
My great uncle painted it.
He was a skilled martial artist
and also a very
talented ink painter.
This should bring us
some good money.
Thank you.
Great Uncle Shinto
always wanted his art
to bring people happiness,
and by selling it,
we will all happily
enjoy a great meal!
Huh?
Yes, that's the way to go, Kori.
Thanks for saving me
from that pickled eggplant!
(laughing)
What a nice attitude adjustment.
Yay, hot beef pot!
(chuckling)
Your lunch is served.
Yoshi, don't just
gulp your food down,
it's unhealthy,
and you'll choke.
(chewing rapidly)
I tried to warn you, Yoshi.
Come on, spit it out,
and you're gonna be just fine.
Instead of beef pot,
order soup next time, Yoshi.
Just shut up and listen.
♪
Democracy will never be
reached by peaceful methods.
Violence is the only way.
Are you saying the
only way to change
is to assassinate
leaders of our government?
We should try to change
things peacefully first,
then if that doesn't work,
maybe we should
try violent means.
Change your thinking.
If it takes acts
of treason, then so be it.
If you keep up
that kind of talk,
then someone's sure
to report you.
Well, I'm not afraid
to crack a few heads.
♪
I believe in democracy, too,
but those guys are
just too extreme.
What do you mean, too extreme?
Unfortunately,
some men think violence
is the only way
to change things.
If they were to try and stop me,
they'd be pushing up daisies.
Bottoms up.
Listen, let's order
another bottle of sake.
Democracy is a really good idea,
but these men are willing
to kill to get what they want.
Too bad our meal's being
ruined by a bunch of drunks.
Let's hope they all just
pass out in a little while.
-Hmm?
(screaming)
(gasps)
Kenshin!
That was quite a blow.
Kenshin, are you okay?
♪
All right, let's go.
That's just great, you start
throwing around dishes,
and because of you,
we have to leave.
Yeah, you clocked
him, you leave.
Excuse me for
interrupting, guys,
but I need to make
a request of you.
Which of you boneheads
was responsible
for hitting my
friend in the head?
What was that?
If I were you, kid,
I'd keep my mouth shut
unless you want to be
spitting out teeth,
so you better just bug off
before you get hurt.
Hey, is that what
democracy's all about?
Apologize!
You better listen closely, kid.
What do you know about anything?
You're just some
smart-mouthed punk
who thinks I won't mop the
floor with ya because you're--
Excuse me.
I'm going to have to
ask you to leave here.
Huh?
What's that?
Get the hell outta here!
(gasping)
I've always thought democracy
was to help the
powerless people,
but I guess the democracy
you guys talk about
is the freedom to behave
like stupid drunks.
Based on what I just
saw you jerks do,
I'd have to say that now
you need to make two apologies.
We're not sorry for anything.
Are you all right, ma'am?
Uh-huh.
You better run unless you're
ready to rumble, skinny.
Maybe you boys need to get
knocked down a few pegs.
(grumbling)
Usually in life,
we try to avoid a fight,
but you three seem
determined to start one,
so I'll oblige you.
You see, I hate people
that pick on the powerless.
I can't stand
when guys like you
talk about
democracy and fairness
and then go around giving
those words a bad name.
So, boys, isn't it about time?
I'd say now is the time.
Okay, you've had it,
let's go outside.
♪
(laughing)
I'm not sure we
should let this happen.
You think I should jump
in and stop this fight?
Don't do it, he's the one
that wanted to challenge them,
so it's his fight.
All right, come on, it's time
to get down to business.
I don't plan on
battling you with my fists.
I'll beat you using my mind.
(grumbling)
That's it!
(grunting)
Now die!
He cheated, he just stabbed
the poor guy with a weapon!
Well, that's that.
That guy got what he deserved
the way he was mouthin' off.
Using a suntetsu
was a dirty tactic,
but it's over.
(grunting)
(groaning)
♪
You don't even have it
in you to fight fairly.
I give up, I give up!
And yet I'm cheating as well.
If I were to use all my power,
there'd be nothing left of you.
So maybe it's best if
I just use one finger.
♪
(groaning)
(groaning and panting)
I hope in the future you'll
be a little more considerate.
How did he do that?
Up until now, you guys have
been getting away with a lot,
but if you're going
to use your sword,
then I will show you no mercy.
Democracy's a good idea,
but before you try to
correct our government,
why don't you correct yourself?
Now pay your bill and
leave here peacefully,
and don't let us see you again.
Kenshin, thanks a lot for
getting them to pay their bill.
They even left a tip!
(groaning)
I'm glad everything
turned out well.
Now all of you can go back
to your peaceful lives.
I just can't stand bullies.
So, how's your head
feeling, swordsman?
Thanks for asking.
Except for a little bump,
I'll be all right.
Glad to hear it.
You knew that bowl
was flying your way,
but you chose not to move
and got that bump.
What?
I know you could
probably sense
that flying rice bowl was
gonna hit you in the head,
but you kept your head
right in the way.
You knew if you ducked,
your lady friend would catch
that bowl right in the face.
Am I right?
You're giving me
way too much credit.
You're smart and humble.
I think I'd like to have a match
with you and really test you.
Thanks for the offer,
but no thanks.
Well, let me know if you
ever have an urge to fight.
I'm living in a shack
near the outskirts of town
if you want to find me.
-See ya.
-Huh?
♪
Boy, he's odd.
From the way he acted,
I couldn't tell
if he was a good or bad person.
All he cares about is fighting.
That's wrong.
He seems good,
but he's a little strange.
Wait a minute!
Oh, so you know him
from somewhere?
That's not it.
He left without paying his bill.
You mean he just ate and ran?
So that's the new
fighter in town
that I've been hearing about?
(laughing)
I could use him to take care
of some unfinished business.
(chuckling)
Hmm.
(dog barking)
So you want me to take
care of this guy, huh?
Well, I'm not an assassin.
I think a man's living or
dying should be left to fate.
I just really enjoy
fighting, that's all.
(sighs)
Like I said,
getting money to kill a man
doesn't interest me.
But I guarantee you,
this job will provide you
with a lot of fun.
That Kenshin is very tough.
Huh.
I think you must be
backing him in this fight
and stand to make
a lot of money if I lose.
Well, I'll give you a hot tip
that might save you
a lot of grief.
Don't bet against me, Gohei.
(laughing)
Who says that I'm betting?
So, you're not in
it for the money.
I just want to see
a royal battle.
I love a good fight.
I think a match between you
and Kenshin would be great.
And there's something
else that you should know.
It's Kenshin,
he has a secret.
He has another name,
a name that I'm sure
you've heard of.
He's Battousai the Slasher.
Are you certain, Gohei?
Positive; here's your chance
to make yourself a name
in the fighting world.
Listen, I'll give you
10,000 yen to fight him,
and when you win,
you'll be famous.
What could be better?
But I don't care
about fame or money.
Huh?
What's important is that I and
my Zanza have a true challenge.
That's what matters.
Huh?
Thank you for this great
opportunity to fight Battousai.
So, the legendary Slasher
will have a chance
to meet my friend Zanza.
♪
Yes.
He's the perfect mercenary
to handle the task
of eliminating Kenshin.
(laughing)
♪
Sanosuke and his Zanza,
a famous fighter
in his own right
in the dark, shadowy world
of underworld combat.
Wherever this lone wolf travels,
he strikes terror in the
heart of his opponents,
and now he's going to do me
a favor no one else can:
take Kenshin out of the picture.
The character painted on his
back couldn't be more true.
He truly is bad.
I hope he makes Kenshin suffer
before he snuffs out his life.
♪
Because of Kenshin,
I can no longer hold the sword
I dedicated my whole
life to mastering.
Watching him die will
be my sweet revenge.
(soft murmuring)
(snoring)
(sipping)
(bell tolling)
Huh?
It's one o'clock.
I must've dozed off.
I really must be
getting home now, Kenshin.
Dr. Gensai, why not spend
the rest of the night here?
Yumi and Suzie are sleeping
so soundly, don't leave!
I'll let 'em sleep on
my mat if you want me to.
Well, you certainly can be
cooperative sometimes, Yoshi.
You know, you didn't have
to say "sometimes," Kori.
Hmm?
♪
There's someone at
your door, right now.
Huh?
At this time of night?
I didn't hear anyone.
I didn't hear him,
but I could feel him.
Oh, oh.
It's someone who
follows his desires
no matter what
the consequences.
It's fighting man.
♪
You're right.
I'm here to fight.
It's the guy we met at lunch.
The guy with the
one-finger punch.
I thought it might be you.
Did you understand me
when I explained earlier?
I don't want to fight you.
I cannot accept that decision.
Tonight, I have come here
to do battle with you,
and considering who you are,
I can accept nothing less.
So, you are
Battousai the Slasher,
a true Royalist
of the Restoration.
That's my reason.
(gasps)
What, how did he know that?
Nagasu sect Royalist
Battousai Himura.
Your preferred technique is
the Hiten Mitsurugi style,
the Flying Sword
to Heaven philosophy.
You flatter me in how diligently
you've studied my career.
Is that part of your
preparation to fight?
Not really, it's just your
reputation is well-known.
But there's a lot of other
things about you I don't know.
For instance,
I heard of it,
but I have no idea
what your Hiten Mitsurugi
style looks like.
♪
I have other
questions to ask you.
What happened to change you
from a cold-hearted slasher
to a peaceful wanderer?
Since you won't
answer my questions,
I guess the only
way to find out
is to fight you
and learn first-hand.
Hmm.
♪
(laughing)
I don't know what
caused me to change.
Huh?
Maybe it was the insanity of
killing people that stopped me,
or having so many people
wanting to fight me
to claim my title.
Allow me to ask you a question.
Why do you continue to
fight wherever you go?
You hate seeing the
powerless oppressed,
yet you insist on fighting
knowing you'll win.
Well, you see, it's because...
It's no use.
It's better not to bring
up melancholy events
that happened in the
past before a fight.
Like many others in your past,
I have come here to beat
you, legendary swordsman.
Battousai must be beaten,
and I will succeed him!
There is no more time for words!
(wind howling)
♪
You know, I don't believe
I've introduced myself to you.
I am Sanosuke Sagara,
and this is my weapon Zanza.
Oh, my gosh!
My sword is named
after where I'm from.
I'm from Zanbato.
Zanbato?
Where in the heck is that?
It's in the north,
a huge sword was built there
and it's designed to
cut an enemy horseman
and his horse in two.
The only problem is no one
has ever been strong enough
to use it effectively.
(wind howling)
(wind stops)
(laughing)
So now finally
the time has come
for there to be an answer to all
of our questions, Battousai.
(shouting)
Kenshin, don't just stand there.
Take action.
(grunting)
♪
(gasps)
That was a very good
counter move,
but it's not over yet.
Now take your sword out.
Do it!
♪
(gasps)
(grunting)
Hmm.
♪
Kenshin.
-Kenshin.
-It's Yumi.
Where are you?
Kenshin?
Are you outside?
You both need to stay inside!
Women and children
should never witness
the savage reality of two men
fighting for their lives.
Sanosuke, do you feel it?
Someone with a bloodthirsty
heart is watching us.
Really?
Huh?
Uh-oh.
(groaning)
What was that?
Really ferocious termites.
Well, you've
dodged me this time.
But you can rest assured
there'll be another time.
Once I get
an opponent in my sights,
it's just a matter of time
until that adversary
is defeated.
Until next time.
(departing footsteps)
What's his motive?
Why does he hate samurai
so much he must kill them?
♪
It doesn't look like he's
going to let me walk away
from this fight
no matter what I do.
It's all right.
I'm glad you're all right.
(giggling)
What was that about?
Hey, I've got news
for both of you.
Come on, Yoshi and I will
carry you two piggyback
all the way home.
(cheering and giggling)
♪
That was our first
encounter with Sanosuke,
but it was just the beginning
of the adventure we would share.
♪
(singing in foreign language)