♪
What the--?
We did it!
It was us!
(laughter)
You two really had me going.
He's so gentle and kind...
he can't be a killer.
Ah, now that's clean!
Oh, now that's really clean!
(laughs)
Ah, it's a beautiful day!
♪
Mmm, it's peaceful.
This feels good.
You need a bath, Kenshin!
Don't get me wet!
Too peaceful.
Come on, let's get charged!
(grunting)
What's that?
How come
there are
no students coming in here?
The Battousai
impersonator incident is over,
so how come martial arts
students aren't joining up?
I know!
After all, I am a cute teacher.
Maybe I'm so beautiful
that students are just
plain scared away?
Maybe it's just
a matter of me being born
under a really unlucky star?
It just doesn't seem fair!
(crying)
How long have you been there?
Sorry.
It's all right.
I know that students
will come back to study
here at Kamiya Dojo, but when?
Miss Kori,
don't get so anxious.
Why not?
You can be a student.
How am I supposed
to keep my skills sharp
if you won't even
fence with me?
No, wooden swords
is not something
that I'm very good at.
Hey, Kori, I'm getting hungry.
I'm starving!
Me, too, so?
Dr. Gensai,
it's good to see you.
Hello, all.
So, what you got for lunch?
Hmm, I've got it!
On a day like this,
we should all be cheerful.
Why's that?
'Cause you're paying
for all of us.
♪
Boy, do I feel lucky!
I just came by to say
hi to my granddaughters.
Kenshin likes
to treat us to lunch.
I'll split some
chow mein with these two.
Chow mein!
Ugh, I think chow mein stinks!
Huh?
Hmm.
Yeah, that's it!
Wait a second!
I haven't moved,
you want that?
Wow, you'll buy that for me?
Sure.
Yay!
I'm glad you're happy.
Huh, what?
Huh?
I hadn't even noticed
that I dropped that.
Huh?
Hey, get your hands off me!
Say, it's nice you gave
him his wallet back.
Kenshin, I knew you'd run off
when it's time to treat us,
now come on!
He could have turned me in.
Look at that man,
he's got a sword!
It's been two years
since wearing one's
been outlawed.
I guess some samurais
just can't let go
of the old ways,
no matter what.
♪
-Huh?
Hey, this kid is a pickpocket.
He stole your wallet.
Hey, ugly, what else can you do?
Yeah?
Well, for starters,
I can tell you
that's no way to talk to a lady,
you purse-stealing punk!
Stop screaming!
Stop, that's enough.
Thanks for catching this guy
and saving my wallet, Kori.
Don't try it again.
♪
Huh?
Let's go.
Kenshin!
♪
Ow!
I'm not just a street kid,
my father was a samurai.
I'm Yoshi Myojin!
I'm a Tokyo fujisoku
and I've never accepted charity
from anybody and
I'm not starting now!
If you think you
and your ugly friend
are helping me
by giving me a break,
guess again!
You two trolls
wouldn't stand a chance
against me if I
decided to fight,
so bug off before you get hurt!
Listen up, kid--
Get it straight,
I'm not a kid!
Please listen, I know
you've grown up fast
living on the streets
by yourself, but you're
still a kid at heart.
I apologize
if I offended you, Yoshi.
One more thing,
no one can ever
take your pride away.
Oh?
Hmph.
That's it, walk away.
Well, one thing's for sure,
he's a big-headed,
ill-tempered young man.
You can tell he's from
a samurai background.
Twenty years ago, he might
have been a great samurai,
but now's the wrong time.
"No one can ever
take your pride away."
I know, but how am I
gonna get out of this?
Hello, Yoshi.
We've been looking
all over for you, Yoshi.
So, come on, give us
the money you made today.
I don't have any!
What?
(grunts)
♪
Haven't I paid you back enough?
Well, I'd have to say no.
In 10 years, maybe 12 years,
or maybe you'd rather have us
cut off your thumb instead?
Waitress!
Yeah, over here please!
So, what do you know
about this pickpocket?
Well, you see, he's an orphan.
Both his parents passed
away when Yoshi was young.
Since then, the head
of the Shigumi has been
taking care of him.
Why the Shigumi?
You see, before she died,
Yoshi's mother was very ill
for a long time
and the Shigumi
covered all
her medical expenses.
So, as a result,
Yoshi owes the Shigumi
an incredible amount of money.
Well, that explains a lot.
So he's forced by those thugs
to work on the street to try
to pay off a huge debt.
Yeah, poor kid.
More hot pot, please!
Yeah, more beef hot pot!
All right, all right.
That's not right,
I can't allow that to happen.
Hold it, where are you going?
To go find that kid,
I can't ignore this!
Wait a minute.
Are you trying to stop me?
I've got to go help him!
Please, Kori.
Kenshin, I can't believe
you're such
a cold-hearted person.
Kenshin!
Go boom-boom.
♪
Now, watch this.
Snake eyes, ha-ha!
They always come up snake eyes?
They're loaded dice,
of course they'll
always come up two.
Yeah, these dice are
gonna make us lots of money.
(laughter)
I said I'm here to see Yoshi!
Who are you?
Did you come here
to try your luck
and gamble with us?
I don't have
anything to say to you.
I came here to talk to Yoshi.
You've got to quit this way
of life before it eats you up.
No matter what the reason,
a pickpocket is
just a pickpocket.
Now, come with me.
But, you see, I can't.
Young lady, so are you
a friend of Yoshi's?
Hmm?
Hey, listen to me!
She doesn't really know me!
Take it easy!
Here is the situation
that Yoshi is in:
He owes us a lot of money
and Yoshi must keep working
for us in order to pay it back.
That is, of course,
unless you are willing
to give us the money
to pay off his debt?
So, how much money
are we talking about?
Okay.
Have a seat.
Huh?
♪
The way we settle debts
around here is to play dice.
Oh.
Don't do it.
Play.
Okay, I'll do it.
But I have two
conditions to play.
Number one,
we only play one roll.
The second condition,
if I win, all of you
will leave Yoshi alone forever.
Agreed, and if you lose at dice,
then your payment
will be to work
as the maid here at
the Shigumi house for 20 years.
Agreed.
Don't do it!
♪
So, let's do it!
Wait, I never asked
you for anything!
Why are you doing this?
It's stupid
to risk your freedom!
Yoshi, just shut your trap.
I'm here to give you some help.
I'm the one that's got
to save you from this
bunch of slime.
Huh?
Hey, you got a lot
of guts for a woman.
But if you lose,
then you're really
gonna have to--
I'm not going to lose, Yoshi.
I've always had
really good luck.
Yeah, I'll win!
I've got such a lucky streak
that I can win
at almost any game.
Quiet down, let's roll!
Yeah, now stand aside!
Even number is "cho,"
odd number is "han."
You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
You call it, okay?
I choose--
Cho.
Han.
♪
It...it can't be!
Han!
I knew it, I won!
How?
I don't understand.
I won, come on,
let's go, Yoshi.
All right, she won,
so I want you to let her go!
You can keep me!
Hey, just what are
you talking about?
You don't understand,
these guys play for keeps.
You'll be lucky to get
out of here alive!
I knew it,
she replaced our dice!
Huh?
So, you're the one?
Hmm.
Hey, now.
Nice try, Yoshi.
Too bad it failed.
Now what, buddy,
you wanna punch me back?
Ooh!
Remember, no one
can take your pride away.
Hit me, hit me all you want.
But from now on,
I don't want anything
to do with you yakuzas.
I'm done working
as a pickpocket
for you lowlifes
and I'm gonna find
myself an honest job
and I'll pay you all
that I owe.
Huh?
Yoshi, that debt you owe us
for your mother's medical care
before she died, it was a lie!
What?
It was a lie we created
so we could own you forever.
There was no debt,
it was just a clever excuse
so you would stay here
and serve us as a dog
the rest of your days!
Damn you!
There you go, dog.
That's too much.
♪
Don't worry, Yoshi,
I can handle 'em.
Now, it's your turn!
♪
Well, your kendo skills
are very impressive for a woman,
but wait, are you ready
to match skills with
Gasuke the Killer?
You men are all alike.
♪
Gotcha!
A dagger stick!
It's time to get serious.
Stop it!
This is my trouble, not hers.
I'll save you!
Wait a moment, Gasuke.
♪
I don't want to see
a woman's blood
spilled during my lunch.
Kumicho?
I want Yoshi right
in front of me now.
♪
Hey, show some respect.
Come on!
Yoshi, how were you planning
to earn a living if you stop
pick-pocketing
and living the street life?
Even if you are samurai-born,
these days that doesn't mean
a hill of beans
in our Meiji era.
Your family pride
won't put any food
on your table for you.
But we have patiently
taught you how to make a living.
It doesn't matter to me
how dirty it may seem to you.
As part of our family,
we will take care of you.
But I've already
explained it earlier.
I don't want to do it anymore.
You'd better watch your mouth
when you talk to komicho.
You now what I think
of your samurai background?
It stinks.
Your dad was stupid to oppose
the government's army
and your mom must've
been brainless, too.
My father sacrificed his life
in order to protect
his feudal lord,
my mother worked hard
to raise me right.
They taught me to be
proud of who I am.
That's why I don't allow
anyone to badmouth my parents!
Got it?
And I won't work
for you ever again!
I see.
Well, Gasuke, Yoshi
is your property,
but I think it's time
to let go of him.
I have to cut my losses.
♪
Stop!
There's no need for bloodshed.
♪
-Huh?
Hey!
I finally found you.
So, just who the hell are
you to come bursting in here?
Well?
Who are you?
Answer!
Men, get in here!
We've got ourselves an intruder!
♪
Your men won't be coming.
They weren't very hospitable
when I asked to come in,
so I had to teach them a lesson
and I put those rude guys
to sleep for a little while.
Really?
Who are you?
I am Kenshin Himura
the Wanderer.
I have come here
to retrieve my friend Kori
and the boy Yoshi
so we can go back
where we belong.
You shoulda stayed at home!
You made a mistake!
Time to say goodbye!
I was still talking.
You need to learn
not to interrupt people.
Whoa.
Sorry about your roof.
Before that interruption,
I wanted to ask you to show
your generosity
of spirit, komicho.
Release my two friends, please.
I think it's
a better choice for you
than losing all your men,
don't you agree?
♪
Sure!
Please, I'd appreciate it
if you'd take them and go!
Thank you,
you're very generous.
Let's go home,
you were hard to find.
I'm glad you finally showed up.
Are you all right?
♪
Why'd you have to come
barging into my life?
Needed to do
a little charity work?
I do fine on my own!
Hey, Yoshi, you like
to handle things your way,
but I couldn't leave something
this important to chance.
Okay, I apologize if my
actions cramp your style,
but you're coming
with me right now.
-Hey!
-Let's go.
You're not leaving!
Yes, let them
leave now, you idiots!
He has the eyes of an assassin!
He's not the kind
that will just kill
out of malice, but you
saw how he dealt with Gasuke!
Those eyes...I never thought
I'd see such a man in this
new Meiji era.
You mark my words,
if he ever gets serious,
he won't leave us just sleeping!
When he gets through,
there won't be enough
of you left to count the bodies.
We'll let him have
the boy, it's a small price,
but he will someday
pay for what he did.
Someday...he will pay.
Darn it!
♪
So, why are you still
beating yourself up
about not being able to handle
everything yourself, huh?
I wish I could've handled it.
I tried to be
as strong as I could,
but it just wasn't enough!
Thanks for saving me.
Even though my parents are gone,
I still wanna make them proud.
You will.
♪
Well, we finally made it.
Welcome to your new home.
You mean it?
Really?
And while you're
staying with us,
you will be learning
the martial art, kendo.
Huh?
Martial arts?
It will help you be stronger.
Mm-hmm!
Yeah, I'll be the best swordsman
this dojo's ever had!
And you will have
the best kendo teacher ever,
a Kamiya Kasshin-style
swordmaster, Ms. Kori Kamiya.
So, what are you babbling about?
Huh?
You gotta be kidding me!
Having her as
a teacher's extreme!
She's so ugly!
All right, just because
I do not have any pupils
does not mean I have to--
Kori?
Just listen,
I'm the one that says when
and who I'll teach, you got it?
Hey, I'd like to see you
spank me if you can,
you big raccoon-face!
♪
I'll get you!
Raccoon!
You're through!
♪
And that's how it happened
that an orphan named Yoshi
from a samurai family
became a member of our family
and joined the Kamiya dojo.
♪