You seem a little
tired today, Mei.
No, I'm fine.
[UME]
If you say so.
I think I'm going to pick up
something for lunch soon.
Is there anything special
you'd like to eat?
Don't be shy.
Remember, we're family!
I want you to tell me what
all your favorite foods are.
[YUZU]
Jeez.
[YUZU] Glad she got
some sleep last night.
I still can't figure
this girl out.
Yuzu, watch out!
Yuzu!
[YUZU]
Huh?
[yells]
[sneezes]
Hurry up and get in the bath,
before you catch your death!
[YUZU]
That's what I'm doing!
[UME]
You should get in too, Mei!
[YUZU]
Huh?
Seriously?
[YUZU]
I guess we are sisters now.
It shouldn't be weird to take
a bath together, should it?
[YUZU]
Her hair's so pretty.
And her complexion is perfect.
I bet her skin is
like super soft, too.
[gasps]
[YUZU]
Wait, what am I thinking?
Why would I touch her skin?
That kiss must've completely
short-circuited my brain!
[gasps]
Uh, I was just about to get out.
Get off!
Just stop.
Why even do something like that?
Well, the way you
were looking at me
made it clear you
wanted to be touched.
[groans]
Where does that weirdo
get off, anyway?
Sure, I looked at her.
Why'd she have to jump to
that conclusion, though?
Hey, it's Yuzucchi!
Y'got bags under
your eyes, girl.
Question.
[HARUMI]
Huh?
I see a lot of couples
at this school.
Are they just playing, or are
they like, "together together"?
[HARUMI]
Oh, them? That's typical.
Whoa, it is?
Yeah, I mean,
it's not like they plan
to stay together
forever or anything.
They just wanna have a little
fun while they still can.
Think about it: A lot of these
girls are already engaged.
Wouldn't you wanna
fool around some
and get that kind
of experimentation
out of your system before
you tied the knot, too?
We're swimming in a sea
of raging hormones.
[YUZU] Okay. Maybe that's
how she feels about me, then.
[HARUMI]
I get it.
You have a crush on
somebody, don't you?
What, don't be stupid!
[HARUMI gasps]
[YUZU]
What's wrong?
[HARUMI]
Ugh, the chairman's here today.
And look at the way
you're dressed!
He is so gonna murder you!
You just stand back and
watch the master, Harumin.
That old coot is no match
for the newly elite Yuzu Aihara!
[HARUMI] Wow, I bet that sounded
a lot cooler in your-- Wait!
Good to see ya, Gramps.
How are you doing today?
And who are you? The nerve!
[YUZU]
Damn, that was cold!
What disgusting
behavior and clothing.
No. Not proper at all.
[YUZU]
Uh. Well, the thing is...
[YUZU] Hello? Did he not get
the memo about me and Mom?
Look, Mei.
Yes, sir.
Explain this thing
to me, please.
How could you let such
a disrespectful creature
disgrace us?
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
[CHAIRMAN]
I see you've been neglecting
your responsibilities
as president.
Now hold the phone!
Why would you go and
punish her for this?
You should be yelling
at me, Gramps!
[CHAIRMAN]
Do not ever, I repeat, ever,
call me by that name again.
You clearly don't
belong at this school.
Get out of my sight! Go home!
[YUZU gasps]
Fine. Consider me gone, then.
Call me a fool all you want,
but if you're too dumb
to listen to other people,
then you're a way
bigger fool than me!
[YUZU] You're a big,
mean old stupidhead,
and I don't even
want you to be...
Who is that
insufferable child?
[YUZU]
Your mustache is dumb too!
[HARUMI chuckles]
I gotta say, Yuzucchi, you
calling the chairman "Gramps"
was like the funniest
thing I've seen all year.
[YUZU] Yeah, well, I never
said it was a foolproof plan.
You sure you wanna sneak in?
Yeah, you bet I do!
I'm not gonna let some old
windbag boss me around.
I might sleep in class,
but I never skip school.
That's still the plan.
Yep. I know, babe.
A teacher.
[AMAMIYA]
Uh-huh. Exactly.
I'm telling you, we'll be fine.
As soon as I marry the
chairman's granddaughter,
money won't be an issue.
I just have to play the
part for two more years.
After that, I'll be
set for a while.
No, don't worry, I'll
still take care of you.
I'd better get back
to work though.
I love you, too, bye.
Uh-oh.
Looks like trouble in paradise
for the student council prez.
First the chairman
yells at her, and now,
her boyfriend's got
a chick on the side?
Wow!
What's wrong?
[MEI]
I'm home.
Hey, can we talk?
[YUZU]
Sorry about today.
I was out of line.
[MEI]
If you're really sorry,
why don't you stop
dressing like a slob?
Really?
Uh, well, take my
apology or don't.
Anyway.
I hate to tell you this,
but I heard Mr. Amamiya
talking to somebody else today.
That jerk face doesn't care
about you like at all.
He's just taking
advantage of you.
The only reason
he's marrying you
is so he can get close to Gramps
and take your family's money
for his real girlfriend.
I get that I'm probably
the last person
you wanna hear this from,
but that guy is bad news.
He's totally using you, and
that's not how love should work!
[MEI]
I know. What's your point?
I dunno.
As your older sister, I think
that's kind of a big deal.
I'm just concerned
about you. Sorry.
[MEI] You're a child
who's never been kissed.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Uh!
Hey! Stop acting like
you're better than me!
I'm trying to look out for you
because that's what sisters do!
[YUZU] She's making
that sad face again.
Almost like she's
in physical pain.
Agh, no fair!
Why am I the only
one who has to deal
with all these crazy emotions?
I feel like such an idiot!
[YUZU]
Look at her.
She's really cute
when she's sleeping.
No, you can't.
Okay, sorry!
Wait. Hold on, is she
talking in her sleep?
Please, Father. Stay.
[gasps]
[MINEKO] And above all,
strive for propriety.
[applause]
[MARUTA] Inspiring words
from Ms. Mineko Fuji...
I wonder where Yuzucchi is at.
No skipping? So much for that.
[microphone hums]
[MARUTA]
What the--?
Hey, you're not
supposed to be up here!
Yeah, I know. This'll
only take a second.
What's she doing?
[YUZU]
Hey, what's up?
My name's Yuzu Aihara,
and I'm a new first year.
Yeah, so, I have a couple of
important announcements
I wanna make if that's
okay with everybody.
And trust me, I hate
long, boring speeches
just as much as the next girl,
so, I'll try to make
it quick, okay?
First off:
Mr. Amamiya made out
with a student,
right here at school, too!
And the worst part of it is...
[gasps]
[YUZU] ...he was totally
forcing himself on her!
Someone stop that girl;
she shouldn't be up there!
[YUZU]
Number two!
I'm the chairman's
granddaughter!
Like, I'm kind of a
big deal around here.
And mic drop!
[chuckles]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[YUZU groans]
I was ready to get
suspended after that,
but I got off scot-free.
[HARUMI] Yeah, well,
as soon as you told everybody
you were the chairman's
granddaughter,
there wasn't a whole lot they
could do to punish you.
[YUZU]
Uh, if you say so.
I'm home!
[YUZU]
Mom?
Are you crying? What's wrong?
I have bad news.
[YUZU]
Huh?
It's about Mei.
They came and took
her away from us!
What?
[YUZU]
I don't understand.
Who do you mean by "they"?
Employees of Mr. Aihara.
They said they were taking Mei
to live with her grandfather.
She didn't argue, either.
She just left without
saying a word.
[YUZU] I did this.
She's gone because of me.
Please don't cry.
We'll figure this
out, I promise!
I'll find out how
she feels about it.
But if she really wants
to stay with her grandpa,
then we're gonna
have to accept that.
Okay?
[YUZU] I'm not just
doing this for Mom.
I also gotta know how Mei
feels about all this.
Yo, President! Have you
got anything to say to me?
Not really.
[grunts]
[SCHOOLGIRL A]
Miss President! Good to see you!
[SCHOOLGIRL B]
Good morning!
[MEI]
Good morning.
[SCHOOLGIRL A]
Oh, hey...
[YUZU] Wow, she
completely blew me off!
[KOBUSHI]
Good morning.
In case you ladies hadn't heard,
Mr. Amamiya had to
leave the academy
due to some personal issues...
[YUZU] Okay, I know I'm kinda
responsible for what happened,
but still, that's no
reason for her to pretend
she doesn't even know me.
How can she go along with
this like it's nothing
when she knows how upset
Mom must be about it?
[HARUMI]
Earth to Yuzucchi!
What's got you feelin'
so depressed, girl?
Well, we do have a
big test tomorrow,
is that what's buggin' ya?
We're high school
students, Harumin.
Tests are just a
part of life for us.
True, but I betcha
I got something
that's gonna turn that
frown upside-down!
Ta-dah!
You remember that
new store? Check it!
[YUZU groans]
Oh, gosh, this is more
serious than I thought.
Sorry, that's cool and all.
I mean, I'll still
take 'em, of course.
[HARUMI]
Don't force yourself.
[YUZU] Not long ago,
that would've made my day.
Maybe I'm turning into
a mindless drone
like everyone else
at this school.
[gasps]
[YUZU] No way! I'm not
giving up that easy!
[YUZU]
Hey, Aihara!
I'm sorry for that
stunt I pulled.
I never imagined
this would happen.
Listen, I probably shouldn't
even ask you, but I have to.
What do you really wan--?
Uh. Is something wrong?
I have a question.
I just wanna know if
you're gonna rescue me
from my mean
grandfather's house.
[MEI]
Just kidding.
My grandfather told me to
stop associating with you,
so I won't be going back home.
And yes, I made that
decision on my own.
[MEI]
Just please leave me alone.
Gym's not your favorite
subject, I know,
but it beats sitting in class
taking a test any day,
don't you agree?
Ease up a little, would ya?
[YUZU] It's been a week, and
she still won't talk to me.
I wish she wasn't always
surrounded by people.
Isn't that girl over there
the one who told everyone
she was the
chairman's granddaughter?
[SCHOOLGIRL D]
What? Like a love child?
[SCHOOLGIRL C]
Probably not.
I bet she made it all up just
to get close to the president.
Really? Creepy.
[YUZU] With the rumors that
have been flying around lately,
I look like some kind
of psycho freak.
Meanwhile, she's as
popular as ever.
We may be technically
in the same family,
but we're a world apart.
This sucks.
What am I gonna do?
[YUZU sighs]
[YUZU]
It's worse at night.
That's when all the
feelings I push away
while I'm at school
crash back into me
like an emotional tidal wave.
[YUZU]
Ugh. I really am creepy.
It's huge!
[MEI]
Why are you here?
[YUZU]
Oh. I, uh...
Your bag.
That's all right.
I'll let myself in.
Oh, wow! What a nice house.
Gramps must be rollin' in dough!
[MEI]
Did you come here just to gawk
at my grandfather's wealth?
[YUZU] No, of course not!
I was just looking around.
[MEI] If that's all,
feel free to leave.
Um, sorry, but are you sure
you're not coming
back to stay with us?
[MEI] So, that's what
you came here to say.
I gave you an answer
several days ago.
My decision is fin--
Fine, then explain something.
Why do you look so
upset all the time?
Like that day you kissed me.
Or when I told you the
truth about your fiancée.
You always have that same
expression on your face.
Do you let everyone see
you sad, or is it just me?
And one night, while
you were sleeping,
I heard you crying and
calling out for your dad.
I just thought, maybe there
was a way I could save you.
Those stupid rules
you've made for yourself
aren't doing you any favors.
You can be free!
There's a better way! I swear!
[MEI]
Shut up.
Look, I know it's
difficult, but I--
That's enough!
Hey, what...?
Stop that!
[YUZU]
Don't be scared!
I'm here, right, here!
[CHAIRMAN]
What's all the commotion?
Keep it down!
[gasps]
Uh, I can explain!
[CHAIRMAN]
I'm appalled at you.
You've been nothing but trouble
from the first moment you
set foot in my school.
In fact, from this moment
on, you are expelled!
[gasps]
I'll file the paperwork.
Get out. Out I say.
[YUZU]
No, wait! Please!
[CHAIRMAN]
Did you hear me? Go.
There is no place for deviants
in my academy or my home.
That place was awesome.
So, where to now?
[YUZU sighs]
[YUZU] My little sister attacks
me, then I get expelled?
What's my life coming to?
What's with you today, girl?
Come on, we planned
to cut loose.
Yeah, that was the plan.
But as it turns out,
it's kinda hard to cut loose
after you've gotten cut off,
if you know what I mean.
[HARUMI]
What?
So, you really are the
chairman's grandkid,
but he expelled you for sticking
up for his other grandkid?
Jeez, talk about a
gigantic load of BS!
I had no idea your life
was such a mess, Yuzucchi.
[YUZU] Tell me about it.
What should I do?
What did your mom say?
[YUZU]
Haven't told her.
Of course not.
[YUZU]
I'm so confused, Harumin.
I do everything I
can to help her,
but it seems like she's more
upset with me every day.
All I wanted to do was
to make her happy,
but I only ended up
causing her pain.
I'm actually a
terrible big sister.
Oh, no, don't say that.
The most important thing is
that you did the best you could.
Any girl would appreciate
having an older sister
who cares about her and looks
out for her the way you do.
Don't worry, I'm sure she
understands how you feel.
How I feel?
[YUZU] All this time, what have
I been trying to say to her?
Oh. I see now.
[YUZU] The truth is, I've
never felt like this before.
I'm beyond clueless about love.
[YUZU] But here love is...
Right in front of me.
[YUZU] I couldn't care less
about what anybody else thinks.
Yes. If you like,
please call me Mei.
[YUZU] Why haven't you ever
called me by my first name?
[MEI]
It's simple.
This was the easiest
way to shut you up.
You know, you're terrible.