[YUZU whining]
[HARUMI]
Hm?
[YUZU whining]
[YUZU]
Why did I do that?
Ugh.
As much as I wish I
could take it back,
it's already been done.
This is all your fault, Mei!
You had to go and kiss me!
I'm sorry I'm such a bad sister.
[YUZU]
Kill me!
I can't believe I just went
and blurted out my feelings!
Man, she must think I'm
like a total creeper!
[HARUMI] Yikes, are you gonna
be okay there, Yuzucchi?
"I'm sorry I'm a bad sister"?
What did that mean?!
Uh, well--
Listen!
Let me stay over at your
place tonight! Please!
[HARUMI]
Hey, it's no problem.
I'll let Grandma know.
But just make sure to tell
your mom where you are.
Thanks, Harumin.
[YUZU]
Jeez.
I wonder if we'll be
able to act normal
with each other after this.
Oh, Mei! You're here!
Yuzu just messaged
to say she's staying
at a friend's house tonight?
Didn't give me much notice.
[groans]
[YUZU]
This sucks!
I've been so hung
up on Mei lately,
I can't do anything else!
So are you gonna, like, tell
me what's bothering you or not?
[YUZU]
Nah, it's no big deal.
I'm sorry to ask you this, but
can I sleep over tonight too?
[HARUMI]
Sure!
Hooray. The VP.
[HIMEKO]
Yuzu Aihara!
[YUZU gasps]
Now what?
[HARUMI]
Uh-oh, what'd you do this time?
I'm sorry, Harumin,
but I gotta go!
[HIMEKO]
Ah!
Not so fast, punk!
See ya?
[HIMEKO]
Don't you run from me!
I will catch you!
[YUZU] Hate to do this
to ya, short stuff,
but I really can't be on
the student council's
radar right now!
I can hear Mei's voice already.
I never want to see you again.
[YUZU]
Not gonna let that happen!
[HIMEKO]
I saw you yesterday!
When you were running
in the hall,
it was because you were meeting
with the president right?
Didn't I tell you I was
gonna catch you?
Now tell me, what exactly
were you doing with her?
All right, I'll spill, but
let's discuss it tomorrow
and literally anywhere but here!
[HARUMI] Shouldn't you go
home and get your stuff?
Sorry. I'm really
putting you out, huh?
It's cool.
Besides, having you around makes
everything more interesting.
Grandma and I get
bored sometimes.
Hello there, Madame.
[YUZU]
Wow, this place is swanky.
[HIMEKO]
Over here, Aihara.
[YUZU]
Hm?
Whoa!
Honestly, it's a shame I have to
waste my precious leisure time
on a lowlife like you.
Ice cream and a Marco Polo.
Just a moment please, Miss.
So, here's the thing,
Vice President.
[HIMEKO]
Himeko Momokino.
Okay, Miss Momokino.
Anyway, was there something
you wanted to talk about?
Oh, please, you know
precisely why we're meeting.
I'll ask again.
What happened between you two
in the chairman's office?
[YUZU]
Guess she's not gonna drop it.
Why is she asking, and how
much does she already know?
[YUZU] Uh, listen, I'm not
trying to like avoid you,
but wouldn't it be better
to ask Mei this question?
Ask Mei?
Yeah, you're on the
student council, so...
[HIMEKO] You and the president
are on a first-name basis?
Just what is the nature of
your relationship with her?!
Relationship's kind of a strong
word, don't you think?
She's my classmate?
Don't play dumb with me!
Our home rooms are right
next to each other!
Of course I know you
two are classmates!
Wait a second.
Why don't you tell me
what you are to Mei then?
I've been the president's
closest friend
since we were children!
We're practically inseparable!
Oh, I had no idea.
She and I have actually
known each other
for more than a decade now.
For as long as
we've been friends,
I've always watched over the
president and protected her.
Mei-Mei! It's good to see you!
[MEI]
Hm?
Oh! Hello, Himeko!
Good to see you!
[HIMEKO] Hey, Mei-Mei, is your
father gonna participate
in Parent's Day with
all the other families?
He can't. The professor is
awfully busy with his work.
Well, I don't think you
need to be sad about it.
Even if he can't come,
I'll still be here with you.
[MEI] It's hard to walk
with your arm like that.
Aw, but, Mei-Mei.
[MEI giggles]
Thank you so much, Himeko.
[HIMEKO] Anyway, why do you
call your father "professor"?
It's kind of weird.
No, it's not.
It makes sense to call him that
because he's taught
me so many things.
I want to learn more, all there
is to know about my family,
so one day I can help him.
Wow, Mei-Mei.
You seem to have a lot of
respect for your father.
That's wonderful!
[WAITER A]
Enjoy your tea.
[HIMEKO] However, we soon
came to a turning point.
After that, the president
started to become more distant,
and kept everything to herself.
Seeing as I'm her
best confidante,
you can imagine how worried
I've been about her.
What was the big turning point?
It happened on the day
her father chose to leave.
Father. Stay.
[YUZU]
Huh.
I wonder what happened
between Mei and her dad.
Anyway, now you understand
why it's imperative
that I watch over
her so closely.
Now, what did you two do
in the chairman's office?
[YUZU]
Um.
What do you think of the way
Mei's been acting recently?
Answer my question first!
[HIMEKO]
She looks completely devastated.
In fact, I haven't
seen her this upset
since the day her
father abandoned her.
[YUZU]
I'm just adding to Mei's pain.
What gives me the right
to force my feelings
onto her like this?
I have no idea what
she's been through!
[HIMEKO]
Get it through your skull.
Why would she want
anything to do with you
when all you can offer
her is suffering?
You should do us all a favor
and get out of her life.
[YUZU]
That's enough.
You can't just leave!
[YUZU]
Tell me something I don't know.
[HIMEKO]
Get back here!
You still owe me an explanation!
[YUZU]
I can't be around her anyway.
[HIMEKO]
President!
[HIMEKO] It's good to see you!
What a pleasant surprise!
Yuzu Aihara requested
a meeting with me today.
And don't worry,
I made sure to give her
a very stern lecture.
[MEI]
When are you coming home?
[YUZU]
I can't.
And why is that?
You live there, right, Yuzu?
[gasps]
[YUZU] Well, yeah, but
it's also where you live.
Will one of you please tell
me the meaning of this?
What's going on?
Sorry, Himeko. I'd planned to
tell you about it earlier.
She and I, well, we're sisters.
[gasps]
[MEI]
I should go.
Right behind you!
Oh, yeah! Momokino!
Thanks for meeting up with me!
[YUZU] Doesn't look like
that made her mad.
As usual, she's a
woman of few words.
But right now, maybe that's
not such a bad thing.
[sighs]
[YUZU]
There's no place like home!
[chuckles]
It was nice to have the bed to
myself for a while at least.
[YUZU] Right, she had the whole
thing to herself for a bit.
Wait, we're in bed together?
I thought she wanted
to sleep separately.
Something wrong?
Nope, not at all!
[YUZU] I should apologize
for what I did, but...
She's completely devastated.
[YUZU] What if I end up
hurting her again?
[MEI]
Yuzu.
Uh, I'm up!
About what happened at
school the other day.
[YUZU] Yeah, I wanted to
talk to you about that.
[MEI] If you're planning
to apologize, don't.
Because I think I may have
pressured you into it as well.
I hear you, Mei, but
I do need to apologize.
I shouldn't have done anything
without considering
how you felt.
So...
You won't let this go until
you get some kind of closure.
I understand that.
[gasps]
[YUZU]
Yeah, that's one way to put it.
Maybe if we, um... I don't know.
[MEI]
Good night.
[YUZU gasping]
And please be quiet.
[UME]
Yuzu! You're up early today.
[YUZU] Yeah, I wanted to
leave for school with Mei.
Gotta make sure
I have enough time
to put my makeup on, don't I?
[UME]
Uh.
[chuckles] Yup, that's my girl.
[YUZU] It's kinda cool to
be up and about this early.
For real. The scenery
is totally different.
Morning, Momokino.
How's it goin'?
[gasps]
What is she doing here?
The president always makes
her morning commute with me!
Are you sure it's acceptable
for the student council
to associate with
troublemakers like her?
It's not a huge issue. No one's
ever around at this hour.
That's not what I
meant, President!
Can I help you?
I just can't get over
the way your hair curls.
Is that really natural?
I told you, yes!
And speaking of appearances,
everything about you is an
affront to our dress code.
Oh, I almost forgot.
You were the one who brought
my bag back to me, right, Mei?
I never said thank you.
[MEI]
Don't thank me for that.
[YUZU] Aw, so modest.
Seriously, thanks.
[MEI] No, my point is
that you should try to be
a little more careful.
If I hadn't taken
your bag first,
it's possible someone else
would've picked it up.
You're free to read any manga
you like, but not on campus.
[coughing]
President, wait! What's
this about a manga?
[YUZU]
Uhh!
Nothing! It's a little
secret between us.
Right, Mei?
[MEI]
I suppose.
[YUZU]
Did you look inside of it?
[MEI]
I made sure it was yours.
[HIMEKO]
That's terrible, Mei-Mei!
How can he just leave his
poor daughter behind?
Don't worry about me, Himeko.
I was the one who decided
that it should be this way.
I have to guard this place,
so one day he'll return.
[HIMEKO] Okay. Until then,
I'm going to guard you.
I promise, Mei-Mei.
I'll never leave you!
[HIMEKO] Since that day, I've
done everything in my power
to keep my promise.
I'm not letting you
take her from me.
[HIMEKO]
After-school inspection's over.
[HIMEKO] All the students
have gone home.
Understood.
Hey, do you remember
back when we were younger?
I used to style your hair
for you all the time.
Yes. I remember that.
You have beautiful hair,
President. I've always loved it.
Long and straight and silky.
I'd trade my curls for hair
like yours in a heartbeat.
You're acting differently.
Something wrong?
[HIMEKO]
I'm the same as I always am.
[MEI]
Himeko!
Your ears are red.
That always has been a
dead giveaway with you.
[MEI] We shouldn't do
this here, Himeko.
We're on school grounds!
We've been friends
for a long time,
there's no reason to be nervous.
No one knows you
as well as I do.
I want you to look at me.
[HIMEKO]
President.
No. My Mei-Mei.
She's late. Unusual.
[MEI]
I'm home.
[YUZU]
There you are! Welcome back!
Let's eat dinner. I made
us some omelets with rice.
Sorry, but I don't think I'm
in the mood to eat anything.
[HIMEKO]
Aihara.
I'd like a word
with you, please.
Someone's popular with
the student council.
Maybe it's a love confession.
Yeah...
[chuckles nervously]
[YUZU]
This is getting old, Momokino.
Just forget about the
chairman's office.
[HIMEKO] That's not
why I called you here.
[YUZU] Really? So it
is a love confession?
I suppose, in a way.
Look, I appreciate
the offer, but--
I'm not confessing to you!
I was alone with the
President yesterday.
We did things we've
never done before.
Did things you've
never done before?
What is that supposed
to mean exactly?
Anyway, Mei didn't mention
any of that to me.
Oh, right.
[HIMEKO]
Why would she tell you?
And I don't care if you
are head-over-heels
in love with her,
'cause Mei-Mei doesn't
see you as anything more
than her big sister,
and she never will.
Nobody said anything about love.
Where did that come
from all of a sudden?
[HIMEKO]
You mean you don't love her?
Then it appears I've
misunderstood the situation.
Excellent.
Well, I do have
something with her,
so we'd like your
complete support.
[YUZU]
No.
Bye, sis.
[YUZU]
That can't be true.
I mean. She did kiss me, so...
Hey, can I talk to you?
You need something?
Earlier today, when Momokino
called me out of class,
she said some crazy stuff
that got me super confused.
So, I was wondering if you
could explain it to me.
Did something happen yesterday?
I don't see what that
has to do with you.
[gasps]
[YUZU]
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Sorry.
[YUZU] Things they've
never done before?
[YUZU] That could mean
all kinds of stuff.
I don't see what that
has to do with you.
[YUZU] Man, she sure
has a lot of secrets.
What is this weird feeling?
Is this what it's
like to be jealous?
The president and I,
we've done some things
you don't know about.
[YUZU]
Sorry, Momokino,
but it looks like this
puts me in the lead.
This is none of your
concern at all.
[YUZU] What Mei needs right
now is not romance.
If that happens, then all
of this will be worth it.