Well, there you are.
Why did you take so long?
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
I had to go home
and change my clothes.
But why? We're supposed to
be out on a date today.
I wish you would
just forget about
all the stupid school rules
for a little while.
Hey, Mei!
[YUZU]
Aw! How cute is this?
[MATSURI] I didn't know you
liked that stuff, Yuzu.
[YUZU]
Hm?
No, I was actually
thinking about it for Mei.
[MATSURI]
Oh. I shoulda guessed.
Whoa.
Hey, watch out. You
almost knocked me over.
Sorry, your body's
just so snuggly!
[MATSURI]
I gotta ask, though.
[MATSURI] Why did you have
to bring her with us?
I dunno. I just thought, uh...
[MATSURI]
Yeah, yeah, say no more.
You've got it pretty bad, huh?
Listen, I already told you,
Mei and I are not like that!
Don't bother denying it, Yuzu.
I know you wanna
do stuff with her.
Like touch her here.
And a few other
places too, right?
Of course not! Don't be weird!
Yeah, okay. In that case.
Good. It's probably not love.
What?
Think about it.
If two girls are super close,
but they're not doing
any sexy stuff,
then aren't they just
friends, basically?
Hush!
That's not quite right either.
You guys are stepsisters.
That's not sexual like at all.
Don't worry, Yuzu.
Maybe she doesn't feel that way,
but you know for sure I do.
I would even have sex with you.
Hey, don't say that in public.
[MATSURI laughs]
[MATSURI]
But I really mean it!
Seriously, I've loved
you for years now,
as long as I can remember.
[MATSURI]
You're mean, Yuzu.
[YUZU]
Matsuri!
[MEI]
What's wrong?
[YUZU] Matsuri just ran
away out of nowhere.
I'm gonna go find her real quick
and see what's going on.
[MEI] Don't you think it'd be
better if I came along too?
[YUZU]
Actually, I should go by myself.
Wait for us where you were,
okay? I'll be right back!
What the heck is her
stupid problem, anyway?
A date is supposed to be
between two people.
Dude, she's gonna murder you.
You're lookin' at her, too.
[ARCADE GAME A]
Game Start!
Why did she have to bring
that student council
bitch along with her?
[ARCADE GAME A]
Owie!
You just had to come
out, didn't you?!
They're only coming out because
you put money into the machine.
[ARCADE GAME A]
That's it, now I'm mad!
"Come out," huh?
Well, there's an idea.
Hey, you two.
[BOYS]
Uh-oh!
I could see you the whole time.
So, you like panties, huh?
I'll tell you what, then...
See, I told you she'd get mad.
Yeah, shut up.
You were doin' it too.
[BOYS gasp]
Come on. Let's make a deal.
Man, where did
Matsuri run off to?
I guess I'll just
keep calling her.
[MATSURI]
Yuzu?
Hey, I'm so happy you
finally picked up.
So where are you? I've been
looking for you everywhere.
[MATSURI] Sorry, I'm not
really at a stopping point
in this game.
I'll meet back up
with you later, okay?
See ya in a bit, though.
[click]
Uh. Did you hang up?
[MATSURI] So, looks like Yuzu
ditched you to look for me.
Apparently, she cares
more about me than you.
Did you speak to Yuzu?
[MATSURI] Yep, we just
got off the phone.
I told her she should give up.
I thought maybe the two of us
could have a chat instead.
One little sister to another.
Wha...?
[YUZU]
Where'd she go?
[MATSURI]
Good, no one'll bother us here.
For real, you can cut the act.
It's obvious you've
been deceiving Yuzu.
You're such a little slut, Mei.
I knew something didn't
smell right with you.
Yuzu always wanted
a boyfriend so bad.
Makes it hard to believe she's
into girls all of a sudden.
See, the thing is,
she's a good person.
Why do you think she
accepted you as you were
right off the bat?
I mean, like even with
all those pathetic,
disgusting fetishes of yours.
You don't care if she's
your own stepsister.
You'll fall for anyone who
can stand to put up with you.
It's unreal.
I can't believe how
easy you are.
[MATSURI] Yuzu is my sister,
so leave her alone.
I don't want you putting
your dirty hands on her.
Are you finished talking?
I've heard enough.
Yep.
You stole Yuzu's kiss.
And now, it's mine.
I should probably
be heading back.
I'm sure Yuzu must
be getting worried.
I suggest you do the same thing.
[laughs]
I can't believe she
just kissed me.
That girl's even crazier
than I figured.
Anyway.
Did you boys get anything?
[BOY A]
Yeah, is this okay?
[BOY B] I know you said
to take a picture
of her hitting you, but...
[MATSURI]
No, I like this even better.
Thanks a lot.
You guys did great.
This is gonna be fun,
in like a weird way.
[ANNOUNCER A] Shoppers, may I
have your attention, please?
Paging middle school
second-year Matsuri Mizusawa,
and first-year high school
student Mei Aihara.
Your party is...
Are they calling for
a high school girl?
Must be up to something.
[WOMEN chuckle]
[YUZU]
Mei!
Jeez, where have you been?
I was like totally getting ready
to send out a search party!
It's times like this I wish
you carried a phone!
I still have to get a
hold of Matsuri, though.
I called her, but
she didn't answer.
I'm really worried.
I'm so sorry, Mei.
I had no idea she was gonna
stir up this much trouble.
It's all right.
Nothing happened.
[phone ringing]
Oh! There she is!
What's up, Matsuri?
What?
[YUZU]
Look! It's snowing!
Man, it's sure got cold fast!
[YUZU] That was totally
rude of Matsuri.
She could've at least
given us a heads-up
before she went home.
What'd I tell you? She's always
acting like such a brat.
And yet, she's still...
important to you?
Yeah. Oh, how should I put it?
The very first day
I met Matsuri,
we had both recently moved
into the same neighborhood.
[UME]
Yuzu?
I'm heading out
to work, sweetie.
[YUZU]
Bye!
See ya later.
Watch the house for me.
Okay!
[chuckles]
Have a good day!
[YUZU]
Hm?
[YUZU] She was a lonely
little girl, too.
As soon as I saw
how alike we were,
I thought it would be nice
if we could be like sisters.
[YUZU] And that's how
we became friends.
But then again,
it might have seemed
completely different
in Matsuri's eyes.
I was pretty bossy
a lot of the time,
so I always thought I
bugged the crap out of her.
[ANNOUNCER B]
We sincerely apologize.
Uh-oh.
[ANNOUNCER B] We are also
expecting several delays
caused by the current snowfall.
[YUZU]
Huh?
I hope Matsuri made it
home okay in this weather.
She left early
because I was there.
I can't help but
feel responsible.
No, no, no, don't worry
about that, Mei, seriously!
There was nothing wrong
with you coming along.
[YUZU] Besides, Matsuri going
home early was my fault.
She invited me to hang
out with her today,
and I kept turning my
attention back to Mei.
I totally understand
why she'd be mad.
I have to find a way
to make it up to her.
[MEI]
I'm sorry.
[YUZU]
Huh?
You look terribly upset,
and that's making me
feel even guiltier.
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU]
Don't be sorry.
I wasn't trying
to bring you down!
[YUZU]
Jeez, get it together!
Why am I being so awkward?
Man, I wish I was
as calm as Mei.
What?
Uh, it's nothing. I'm fine.
[YUZU]
No, wait. Mei only looks calm!
She's always acting like
a huge weirdo, remember?
Cold on the outside,
but intense on the inside.
[YUZU]
Hey, Mei?
It's really cold, huh?
Do you think we
could hold hands?
It's probably okay for sisters
to do that much, right?
I suppose.
[YUZU]
Oh my god, I'm so happy!
Your skin's so warm.
But then again, it always is.
When we started sleeping
in the same bed,
it was so hot,
I couldn't tolerate it.
But now that the
weather's turned cold,
it's actually pleasant.
Totally.
[MEI]
It's strange.
I'm constantly seeking out
warmth from other people
because I'm so
messed up on my own.
[YUZU] Well, I can't speak
for everybody, but...
All I know is that
if you're messed up,
then I must be like the
biggest disaster ever.
Look at me.
Always wanting to touch
you, or waiting for you...
[MEI]
Yuzu.
Looks like the buses
have quit running.
Why am I telling you all this?
Really?
Crap, we were
waiting for nothing.
Then, let's walk.
I hope it'll snow on
Christmas this year, too.
So, you do Christmas?
Interesting.
Yeah, my family puts on
a giant party every year.
And this time is special
because you'll be there.
So, make sure you put it
on your calendar, okay?
All right, I will.
[sighs]
How disappointing.
While everyone else
is getting ready
to enjoy the Christmas season,
we're stuck at school working
on the budget for next year.
[MARUTA]
Don't be upset.
It won't take much longer.
We'll have our snacks
and cake in no time.
Focus on that.
Plus, having something
fun to look forward to
keeps me motivated!
You sure do love to eat,
don't you, Maruta?
You've got a point, though.
I'm most likely
feeling impatient
because I'm eager to
spend the holiday season
with the president.
[MARUTA] That's true,
and you first-years
have your school trip
coming up in February too.
Precisely! I must
solidify our bond!
She'll forget all
about Yuzu Aihara
and spend the whole
trip alongside me!
[MARUTA giggles]
See, I knew you would find
a way to get motivated!
Just picture it.
Alone together on Christmas,
discussing our plans,
right under the mistletoe.
I'm sorry to interrupt
you. I'll be brief.
Oh! President Aihara. How
much of that did you hear?
It's about the
year-end schedule.
Can we finish things
up by the 23rd?
I was hoping to be off
after closing ceremonies
on the 24th, if possible.
[HIMEKO]
Looking at the workload,
I think that can happen, sure.
But I'm surprised, President.
You've never been one to
rearrange the schedule before.
I know that, but I have
a family function.
I'm sorry to make
a selfish request
during such a busy
part of the year.
There's no need to be
concerned, though,
and I'll finish the rest
of this work tomorrow.
Is that really all you were
worried about? Just relax!
You have us on
your side, remember?
Go ahead and enjoy yourself.
We'll take care of
everything on this end.
This is a special Christmas.
It's your first one with
your new family, right?
Go spend time with them.
I mean, your whole family!
I'd better not find
out it's just you
and that Yuzu Aihara
girl together!
Please try to calm down,
Vice President.
[HIMEKO]
Have a good time, okay?
[MEI]
Thank you.
Looks like it's not gonna be
a white Christmas
this year, after all.
Eh, that's okay.
[HARUMI]
Hey, Mama! Please buy these!
Nah. You don't need 'em.
[HARUMI]
You're so rude!
I make a joke and you
just shut me down?
Sorry, but I don't have time
for the whole comedy
routine today, Harumin.
[HARUMI whines]
[HARUMI grunts]
[GIRL A yelps]
Aww! I wanna go to the
Christmas party! Can I?
I can't do that. It's a
family-only thing. Sorry.
[whines]
[HARUMI]
Hm?
You're really getting
into this, Yuzucchi.
Making all that by hand?
[YUZU] I never made a
cake from scratch before,
but I really wanna try.
The rest of the recipes
are pretty standard.
It'll work out okay. I think.
Wow, color me impressed.
Besides the few things I
picked up from Grandma,
I suck at cooking.
With all those domestic skills,
you'll be a great wife someday.
[YUZU]
A wife, huh?
You know, I kinda like
the sound of that.
[door opens]
We're all finished!
We've thoroughly inspected
the school grounds.
[MEI]
Thank you.
Isn't it about time
for you to go home?
Let me walk with you.
No, that's all right. I'll be
here a while. My apologies.
Well, if that's what you want.
Have a nice night, then.
[YUZU]
Hmm...
Ooh. I'll borrow this!
There!
Don't you get exhausted working
so late all by your lonesome?
Are you surprised
to see me again?
Come on. You wanna
warm me up, yeah?
Like you did for Yuzu.
[MEI] She'll never go back
to the way she was.
[MATSURI]
Yeah, but that's okay.
She'll always be
my older sister.
[MEI] That girl desperately
needs you, Yuzu.