[MEI]
Professor? You're... back.
Uh, did you just call
this guy "professor"?
[SHOU]
I thought I told you
to drop the whole
"professor" thing, Mei.
I'm not a teacher anymore.
Maybe try "Dad" instead?
What? So you're Mei's father?
Wait, that means...
Are you my dad, too?
Nice to meet you!
[YUZU]
If he's back,
then Mei doesn't have to
work all the time anymore!
This is perfect!
[YUZU] Oh, that's right. They're
not on the best of terms.
[SHOU]
Here.
Goodnight.
Uh! Wait a second! C'mon, Mei!
[YUZU]
Here goes.
It's okay, Daddy. Mei's
just tired, that's all.
I mean, she did make
student council president
in her first year.
Superstars like your daughter
tend to get worn out.
Please, stop.
She's been covering for Gramps
since he's out so you
could still take over.
--Sweet, right?
--Be quiet!
Why? What's wrong?
[SHOU] I'm sorry, but I'm not
goin' back to the school.
[YUZU]
What?
Hold on, don't go!
Come out! Please!
Well, that's great.
I said something
I shouldn't have again.
Nah, it was my fault.
Sorry for getting you involved.
[SHOU]
Hmm...
We'll have to give
this big guy a name.
But for right now, let's
go grab some dinner.
[SHOU] Mei loved these
when she was little.
You think she still does?
[YUZU]
Yeah, as far as I know
she has a pretty
big sweet tooth,
so I'm sure she'll
appreciate them.
Last time she and I
went out on a da--
Uh, I mean, the last time
I hung out with her,
we had crepes.
[SHOU]
Good to hear.
I can tell you like
Mei a lot, Yuzu.
Uh, I dunno, like is kind
of a strong word--
[SHOU]
Thank you.
I'm grateful you're
lookin' after my girl.
[SHOU]
I see.
So she's still
tryin' to make sure
I can come back to the
academy eventually, huh?
Because if he decides not
to return to the academy...
[SHOU] I'd always rather
look ahead than look back.
Mei doesn't understand
why, but I can't stay.
There's just so much of the
world I haven't seen yet.
Oh.
She's a smart girl though,
so it shouldn't take her as long
to figure it out as it took me.
There is no "right"
path to take in life.
You can't see it, till you've
already traveled down it.
[SHOU]
We should head home.
[YUZU]
Huh...
In his own weird way,
he does have her best
interests at heart.
They're just having a hard
time understanding each other.
[YUZU]
I'm home, Kumagoro.
[YUZU] And now that I know a
little more about the problem,
maybe there is
something I can do.
[YUZU clears throat]
Hey, Mei? Are you in there?
Listen, about earlier.
I was stupid.
I shouldn't have gotten
all carried away.
I promise I wasn't trying
to embarrass you and stuff.
I just wanted your dad to
know that he should be proud--
[MEI]
Stop. It doesn't matter now.
Why?
Because the father
I admired so much,
he was a very strict
and disciplined person.
[MEI] He always put the academy
before his own happiness.
He held everything and
everyone to a high standard,
even his daughter.
I wanted to be like him.
I thought it was the path
I was supposed to follow.
So when he divorced my
mother, I accepted it.
I always hoped that that version
of him would return to me.
Which is why, five years
ago, I chose to stay
in the Aihara household
instead of going with him.
I swore I'd protect the place
where my father would return.
Mei.
Jeez, when are you gonna stop
trying to do everything alone?
I had no choice.
Nobody else was around to
take care of the academy.
[gasps]
And now that my father
doesn't need my help,
who's going to give
my life any purpose?
[gasps]
Mei, I...
[YUZU]
Whoa.
Hey! What's up with you?
Tell me honestly, Yuzu.
You'll be the one who
needs me, won't you?
You want to do things
with me, right?
Please say yes, Yuzu.
I'm lost. I need someone
to accept these feelings.
Oh, Mei.
It didn't take me very
long to convince you.
I'm surprised.
[MEI] Tell me what you want.
I'm good at taking orders.
It doesn't matter
what I do anymore.
But I'll be gentle though,
since it's your first time.
[gasps]
What's your deal, huh?
Why can't you think of
my feelings for once?
[YUZU] So you travel all over
the world teaching people?
[SHOU]
Yep.
I quit the school where you go,
and now I'm building
another one somewhere else.
Why'd you choose
to live that way?
As soon as I figure that
one out, I'll let ya know.
[SHOU laughs]
[door opens]
[YUZU]
Huh?
Hey, Mei. Don't leave!
What about breakfast?
Jeez.
[SHOU] Sorry. I've probably
made things awkward for you.
Can't you two talk things over?
Your father's a very
complicated person, Yuzu.
Really?
He shows so much love
and care for children
all around the world,
but his own daughter's
the one that stumps him.
Shou really does care
about Mei though,
even if he has a funny
way of expressing it.
[SHOU grumbles]
Thank you, dear.
[UME] He keeps coming back
because he's worried about her.
But then he always manages to
find a way to make things worse
and ends up getting
all grumpy about it.
Wow, that's lame.
Ugh, quit rakin' me
over the coals, Ume.
You're right, though.
I left when Mei really
needed a parent the most,
and if I talked to her
about it now,
I'd probably just
confuse her more.
Our family's not
great with feelings.
Oh.
[SHOU]
Yuzu.
I need you to support her, okay?
[YUZU] I know she's
hard to connect with,
but I still think he should try.
[bike bell ringing]
[HARUMI]
Hey, slowpoke! Don't be late!
Harumin! You took
a bike to school?
Gimme a ride!
[YUZU] He's totally
overcomplicating this.
[YUZU] I guess all parents
can't be as laid-back
about that stuff as my mom is.
It seems like President Aihara's
feeling a little under
the weather today.
[SCHOOLGIRL B] Yeah, she ignored
me when I tried to talk to her.
[SCHOOLGIRL C] She's even
beautiful when she's sad!
I do hope she feels
better though.
Hey, Yuzucchi, get your butt in
a seat, the teacher is coming!
'Kay.
[YUZU]
I dunno.
I yelled at her for
ignoring my feelings,
but maybe I'm the one who
doesn't understand hers.
[YUZU] I wish I knew
what to do for her.
Before, I thought
what she needed
was for me to be a good sister.
Maybe she just needs her dad?
Or maybe it's something else?
Man, this is hard.
[HARUMI laughing]
[YUZU]
What's so funny all of a sudden?
You've been making this goofy
face all day, Yuzucchi.
Reminds you of a zombie, right?
[HARUMI laugs]
Oh my god, what a loser!
I've been dealing with a family
crisis, thank you very much!
Okay, okay, I'll stop.
It seems like you are working
through some serious drama.
[whines] Please help me!
[HARUMI]
Aww.
Don't worry. Whatever it is,
I'm here to comfort you.
Now, come to my bosom, child!
It's all right.
Mama Harumin knows you're
doing the best you can.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah, that makes sense!
What does? Did you find
the answer in my boobs?
Well, not exactly.
[phone ringing]
[YUZU]
Hey, Mom, what's up?
Hi, Yuzu. Are you
free right now?
[YUZU]
Yeah, everything okay?
Please tell me Mei is with you.
Mei? No, why're you asking?
[UME] I just talked
to Shou, and, well,
apparently he's planning
to leave the country
again this evening.
Huh?
[UME] I asked the academy
to tell your sister,
but they couldn't reach her.
Sorry, hun, but can
you see him off?
[YUZU]
Where is he?
He's getting ready to
head to the airport now.
I think he said he was
catching the 6:40 train.
[YUZU] I can't let them miss
their chance to fix this!
[gasps] It's five? Already?
[HARUMI]
Yuzucchi!
Hop on!
Wait here, Harumin!
'Kay!
Mei, you here?
Sorry, Aihara.
but I believe she already
left for the afternoon.
What? Are you sure?
I just looked and her shoes
are still in her locker!
Oh, my. That's quite unusual.
[YUZU]
Sorry! Gotta go!
[HIMEKO]
Uh. Hold on!
[YUZU]
If she keeps running away,
then nothing's ever
gonna change!
Mei!
[YUZU]
Come on, Mei. Where did you go?
Professor.
[SHOU] I'm sorry I had
to miss Parents' Day.
Oh.
[gasps]
Back at the amusement park,
you had your eye on that bear.
I wasn't sure what else to get.
Wow, thank you.
You're welcome.
So do you know what
you're gonna name him yet?
Let me think.
How 'bout "Bear"?
[SHOU chuckles]
Well, we can work on the name.
Aw, man!
[ANNOUNCER A]
The school is now closed.
Any students still on campus,
please switch off all
lights, lock all doors,
and be careful on your way home.
I repeat: The school
is now closed.
Any students still on
campus, please-- Ah!
What are you doing?
[YUZU]
Listen to me, Mei!
I've seen how hard
you work for your dad
and for this academy!
You've sacrificed so much!
And you're doing an awesome job.
So please stop beating
yourself up, okay?
You have to live life for you,
not everybody else.
So, come on. Let's go
say goodbye to your dad.
I'll be waiting!
Of all the nerve! Your
delinquency knows no bounds!
They could expel you
for a reckless stunt
like that, you know!
Though I admit, that
wouldn't be disappointing!
[MEI]
Yuzu.
[BOTh gasp]
[HIMEKO]
President!
[YUZU]
Clock's ticking!
[MEI]
Yuzu.
Why do you always make
these dramatic decisions
without thinking?
[YUZU]
I am thinking, Mei!
I thought a lot about how
I could make you happy
and this is what I came up with!
That doesn't really answer
my question though.
[YUZU]
Fine, there is no right answer!
I'm doing this because
I wanted to, end of story!
[YUZU]
Excuse us!
I'm pretty sure that his
train hasn't left yet!
Over there!
[SHOU gasps]
It's Yuzu. And Mei?
[YUZU]
Go on. Say bye.
Um, Profes--
[gasps]
See ya later, Daddy.
Have a good trip!
Travel safely.
Bye, Dad.
[YUZU chuckles]
[YUZU]
You better come back soon!
[laughing]
[MEI]
Yuzu.
Yeah?
[MEI] I'm going to inherit
the academy someday.
Because it's what I choose.
Sounds like a plan.
[YUZU]
Don't worry, Dad.
Mei's headed in the
right direction now.
[YUZU]
So, what kind of conversation
were you guys having?
The same one we had before.
Except for this time,
I was mature enough
to understand what
my dad was telling me,
and the reason he had to leave.
He left our family
because the path he chose
was that important to him.
It makes sense now.
[YUZU crying]
What's wrong?
Why're you crying?
[YUZU]
I dunno.
I guess it's because
I'm relieved.
I'm sorry.
This is your big moment,
and I'm the one who's a mess.
[BOTH gasp]
[YUZU]
Whoa. What just happened?
For some reason,
that kiss felt way different
from all the other ones.
[MAYU crying]
[MAYU]
Matsuri.
I don't... think I can
go on without him!
I don't understand
what's wrong with me.
Aw, there's nothing
wrong with you, Mayu.
You're cute, and he's
stupid for dumping you.
You're a good friend, Matsuri.
Aww.
[MATSURI] Yeah, right.
She's just as dumb as he is.
Bye forever.
[MATSURI]
Yuzu.
That takes me back.
Wonder how she's been.
[MATSURI]
I've got nothing to do.
Maybe I'll pay Yuzu a visit.
[YUZU]
I need you to be clear.
What did that kiss mean?
Nothing.
Yuzu! Found ya!
[YUZU] If you don't go
to an all-girls' school,
two girls kissing
might be unusual.
[MATSURI]
Hey, Yuzu.
Do you have a crush on anybody?