[YUZU]
Uh.
Ah, jeez, it's
stupid Momokino.
[grunts]
Great, it's Yuzu Aihara.
Hello, slob. Exactly where
do you think you're going?
Mei forgot her lunch
box this morning
so I just wanna make sure
she gets to eat something.
Why would you do that right
after I instructed you
to keep your distance from her?
Sorry, but we live together,
what'd you honestly expect?
Right.
In that case,
why are you carrying around
two lunch boxes, then?
You don't need
yours to deliver hers.
[YUZU] If we're
playing 20 questions,
why do you eat in the
student council room?
You can't tear yourself
away from work, can ya?
[HIMEKO] You're fighting
a war you can't win!
The president and I did things.
We've crossed lines that
you're never gonna cross.
[YUZU gasps]
So? Big deal!
I'll so cross lines. Don't
tell me how to live my life!
[gasps]
[HIMEKO]
Uh!
Don't you run from me!
--[YUZU] Mei!
--[HIMEKO] President!
[HIMEKO, YUZU chattering]
Oh, come on!
At least let her take a
break to have some lunch.
Whatever, it'll be more
efficient this way.
We have a lot of work to do,
and we can't do that
with you around.
Listen, you.
[MEI]
Quiet.
You two go eat lunch together.
I have work to do.
I need peace and quiet.
Way to go.
You just had to barge in
and start bothering her.
How can you accuse
me of something
that's so obviously your fault?
[YUZU] Wait. Why did she
get mad at both of us?
Momokino says they've crossed
some kind of line together,
but she doesn't seem to be
getting any special treatment.
[HARUMI]
Hey, Yuzucchi!
Whatcha doin' in the cafeteria?
Thank goodness
you're here, Harumin.
[HARUMI]
This is a weird combo.
Since when are you
friends with that?
How absurd. Do I look like
I'd be friends with a hoodlum?
[HARUMI]
Check it out, girl.
I got theme park tickets.
Wanna go with me?
[YUZU]
Sure, okay.
I'm thinking, like, next Sunday.
Our exams are coming up.
This is hardly the right
time for goofing off.
[HARUMI]
So you wanna come with?
Why would I do that, huh?
Oh, if you're on board,
we might as well invite
the president too.
[HIMEKO, YUZU]
Really?
Okay. What's up with
the weird double act?
[YUZU] It won't be a date
with all four of us,
but it would be nice
to go there with Mei.
[HIMEKO] I highly doubt
the president can make it.
Not only does she have her
normal student council duties,
but she's covering
the chairman's work
while he's in the hospital.
She works every
waking hour these days.
Uh!
You just--! That's basically
a kiss, you know!
[BOTH]
Huh?
It's indirect, but still--
I think those curls of
yours are too tight, girl.
Loosen up and try
something different.
[YUZU] I never thought of
kisses that way before,
but Mei and I could do it.
[YUZU]
No, that's way too forward!
The next step is to spend a
little quality time with her.
[YUZU] I guess there's no
harm in asking her, right?
[HARUMI]
Hm?
[HIMEKO] Ugh. I'll make a
note of it in my calendar.
[YUZU]
Tomorrow's when I visit Papa.
I was planning to do it
by myself like usual,
but maybe it'll be
a perfect chance
to get a bit closer to Mei
before we all go
to the theme park.
[YUZU] Besides, I'd like
to introduce Mei to him.
I'm sure he's not
gonna mind that.
[YUZU]
Huh?
I'm home!
[UME]
Hey, Yuzu!
Is Mei back home, yet?
[YUZU]
Mei?
You got a letter in the mail.
Looks like it's from your dad.
I wonder where he sent it from.
Should I maybe open it?
Huh?
[MEI]
Stop!
Whoa, I'm sorry!
I wasn't actually gonna
open somebody else's mail.
Don't worry, I'll go put it on
your desk for you right away!
[YUZU] That scared me.
She was super mad!
[YUZU]
Uh, Mei?
[MEI]
What?
[YUZU] Aren't you gonna
read your letter?
[MEI]
It's none of your business.
[YUZU]
That's fair.
Anyway, do you think maybe
I can borrow you tomorrow?
I was hoping you'd come
with me to meet my dad.
[MEI]
And why is that?
Mom said she wanted
you to go, so...
[YUZU]
Great, now I'm liar.
[MEI]
All right then.
If it's important
to her, I'll go.
[YUZU]
Sorry, Momokino,
but I guess this puts
me in the lead.
[YUZU sighs]
If this keeps up, I'll literally
never get any sleep.
[HIMEKO] Why did I
volunteer to invite her
when I know she won't come?
Now I'll be the one who's
going to look flakey.
[UME]
Hello?
Yes. Good day.
This is Mei's most treasured
friend Momokino calling.
Is she the--?
[UME] Oh, I'm sorry,
you just missed her!
She's out with Yuzu right now.
What? Curse that Yuzu Aihara.
She's going to pay
dearly for this insult!
Something the matter?
I just got chills for
some weird reason.
[YUZU] Almost like
someone's watching me.
[gasp]
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU]
It's all in my head.
This is my first date with Mei.
No one can get in my way.
[YUZU]
Hey! Mei!
Where'd you go?
[YUZU]
Not a great way to start off.
I have to look out for her!
[YUZU]
I've got you!
[MEI gasps]
Um, please, don't breathe, okay?
Don't breathe?
What, do you want me
to die or something?
[MEI gasps]
Whoops. Did I step
on your toe, or--?
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU]
Wow. Her body's so warm.
Come on, tell me.
[MEI gasps]
[YUZU] Maybe this is my moment
to cross a line with her.
[YUZU]
Uh, now what do I do?
[MEI]
Hey! Stop fooling around!
This is a public setting.
Control yourself.
I'm serious!
I really wanna
be with you, okay?
Um, what do you mean?
It's just... Momokino, she...
She said that you
guys, um, you know...
Look, Mei. I'm sorry!
But I can make it up
to you with crepes.
[MEI]
It's not that I'm angry.
But you are a human being,
so you have to learn to
control yourself like one.
[MEI] Also, I don't know
what sort of ideas
you've gotten into your head,
but there's nothing between
Himeko and myself.
Then why did she say
all that stuff about
how you guys "crossed
some sort of line"?
[MEI] Himeko tried to do
something inappropriate
and I scolded her.
And that's all there is to it.
I'm sure she twisted
things to suit her purposes.
Though, you should have been
able to see through that.
[YUZU]
Good to hear!
[YUZU] Awesome! So I still have
a shot with her after all!
[MEI]
You seem to be happier now.
[YUZU]
You're happy too, right, Mei?
I mean, it's cool that your
dad sends you letters.
I bet he loves you a lot.
[YUZU]
Uh-oh.
Uh. Never mind that!
There's no reason to
think about it too hard.
You should just enjoy your crepe
and forget that I
even brought it up.
[YUZU]
Oh, yeah!
We could totally do that
indirect kiss thing!
This place is amazing.
All the desserts they make
here are so delicious.
Do you mind if I try a
bite of what you're--?
[YUZU]
She already finished it!
Well, you can at least
have a taste of mine!
Sure. I can sample a
little from this piece.
[YUZU]
Man. Why am I so hung up on Mei?
I think I love her.
I wanna kiss her.
So, uh, Mei?
Is it maybe okay with
you if we hold hands?
[HIMEKO]
Hold it right there!
[YUZU]
Oh my gosh, it's Momokino?
[HIMEKO]
So this is where you were!
How the heck did
you find us here?
Pucchi! Good dog.
[HIMEKO]
Don't think for a second
I'll let you get ahead
of me, Aihara!
[HIMEKO growls]
I'm certain you must've
forced the president
--to go out with you toda--
--[MEI] Himeko.
Did I say something wrong?
This is none of
your concern at all.
Stop deceiving Yuzu.
It's disgraceful.
Sorry, Mei-Mei.
[MEI]
Let's go.
[YUZU]
Uh, okay.
This is the place.
[MEI] I didn't realize
your father had passed.
Oh, yeah.
He's been gone ever since
I was only three years old.
It's fine! I've made
my peace with it.
See? Look.
Papa, this is my little sister.
Let me introduce you to Mei.
Yeah, I know.
I guess it's kind of weird
since she is taller
and smarter than me,
but she's also pretty awkward
and rough around the edges too.
Anyway, what I'm really
trying to say to you is,
just like you've
always protected me,
now I have somebody to
protect and look after.
Well, I guess that
concludes today's mission!
You wanna get something to eat?
Oh, sorry!
[YUZU] Papa, I need you
to lend me some courage.
[YUZU]
Mei!
I, uh, I want to--
The letters my father sent...
I've never opened them.
I'm afraid to find out
what he's thinking.
Because I'm worried
he may decide
not to return to the academy.
Is it possible?
Can I...? Can I be ever
close with him again?
[YUZU]
Uh.
Are you kidding? Why not?
I mean, you've got
me to help you!
We'll make it happen,
I promise you!
Guess it's time to go home.
[YUZU crying]
[YUZU] Man, after the
way she looked at me...
How can I kiss her now?
[YUZU] What Mei needs
right now isn't romance.
It's support. From her family.
[YUZU]
That's it.
I'm just gonna give
up on the love thing
and focus on being her sister.
[HIMEKO gasps]
[HIMEKO]
Are you hurt?
[MEI]
Keep your voice down, Himeko.
I just tripped.
I think, maybe
you're sick, President.
Perhaps you shouldn't attend
the meeting after all.
Don't be silly.
I have to be there.
[HIMEKO]
You look like you're burning up!
Let me get you some help.
Drop it, Himeko!
It's not like you
can take my place!
Hold up! That was rude,
even for you!
She's only getting on your
case because she's worried!
Yes, I'm aware. I don't
need you to tell me... that.
--[HIMEKO] Oh, no!
--[YUZU] Whoa, watch out!
[HIMEKO]
She fainted!
Stay here! I'll go
get the nurse!
[YUZU]
Wait!
Isn't that council
meeting important?
You should go.
Well, yes, but that's
not the issue here!
[YUZU]
Maybe not,
but I bet it's the biggest
thing on Mei's mind.
Please, Momokino,
do it for her.
[HIMEKO]
If you insist.
[MEI]
Where am I?
[YUZU]
Nurse's office.
You have a fever,
so you need to rest at least
until the nurse gets back.
No, you're not going anywhere!
The student council's waiting!
And then there's
a board meeting!
I need to be there!
All those things are exactly
what made you pass out!
It's just like with Gramps.
[MEI]
I've heard enough. Let me go!
You might as well give up.
[YUZU] I'm sorry I made you
go with me to see my papa.
Some sister I am.
[MEI]
Oh? You're being sisterly now?
Don't worry. It was my decision.
You don't have to apologize.
[YUZU] Why have you been working
yourself practically to death?
I mean, most teenagers
in high school
don't even have to work at all.
[MEI]
I'm the successor.
Who cares about that?
You're a teenager! Can't your
dad help with that stuff?
Hey, I know!
Your dad can be the successor.
There's no reason
you should have to
bust your butt like
this, you know?
Huh?
I actually agree with you.
You're always running
your mouth,
but once in a while,
you make a legitimate point.
It's only temporary, though.
When the time comes,
I know all this struggling
will have been worth it.
[YUZU]
He must be really special.
She's never looked at me
with that much love before.
If I can be the best,
most supportive big sister
in the world,
I wonder if she'll start to
see me in a different light.
Well, anyway, we're gonna
get that fever down
so you can be healthy and
back in action real soon,
and I'll start by taking
your bags down.
Oh, yeah! As far as Momokino...
What about her?
[YUZU] I'm sure your fever
probably had you all hazy,
but you still said some super
mean stuff to that girl.
You need to apologize
as soon as you're well.
Seriously, make up with her.
We've got a theme park to go to!
What was that about?
[YUZU] Mei obviously needs
her dad to be with her.
Why's he out traveling
the world anyway?
[YUZU]
Huh?
[HIMEKO] Mei-Mei's always
been the kind of person
to shoulder all of her
problems on her own,
ever since she was
a little girl.
I knew for a fact she was
feeling under the weather...
...but I couldn't mention it.
If you ask me,
you're a lot like her
when it comes to
taking on too much.
So maybe try cutting
yourself some slack
for once in your life.
Yeah, that's easy
for you to say.
Not everyone can be
as flippant as you are.
[YUZU] What Mei needs
right now isn't romance.
It's support. From her family.
Yeah, right. I only wish I could
be so flippant about all this.
[MEI sighs]
[HIMEKO crying]
[HIMEKO]
Mei-Mei!
[YUZU] Letting go of your
feelings for someone
because you love them...
[YUZU] This is more complicated
than I ever imagined.
You know, I should sign
up for student council.
Maybe then I could help
lighten the load for everyone.
If we had you there,
then we'd be dealing
with even more trouble.
Here's a thought.
Follow the rules before
trying to enforce them.
Well, fine, I see how it is.
[door opens]
[YUZU]
Mom?
Hey, how was your day? Uh.
[YUZU]
What the--?
[SHOU]
Surprise!
I've finally returned!
Uh, who are you?
[SHOU]
Ah, you must be Yuzu.
Yeah, but I don't know
who the heck you are.
Your mom's right!
You are so adorable!
[SHOU laughs]
[SHOU] I was wondering
when I'd get to meet
the spunky girl I've
heard so much about!
C'mere, you!
[YUZU]
What are you doing in my house?
Take those grubby hands off me
or I'm calling the cops!
How do you know my name, anyway?
Are you some kind of
psycho stalker creep?
Seriously, you need to let
me go or you'll regret it!
I swear, you're about to
be in a world of pain!
Uh, Professor?
What? This perv
is your father?
That means, he's my father, too!
[MEI]
It doesn't matter now.
Stop trying to do
everything alone!
Tell me honestly, Yuzu.
You do need me, don't you?
[YUZU] There's gotta be
some way I can help Mei.