[gasps]
That's fine.
[SARA gasps]
Huh?
The girl you're
head-over-heels about,
she's also my sister's destiny.
[YUZU]
I get it.
[NINA] At first,
I felt bad for all this,
but now I'm glad I decided
to stick my neck out.
You made a promise, remember?
She's in love,
and you told me you
were gonna support her.
[YUZU] I can't believe Mei is
the girl Sara's in love with.
[NINA]
That said,
I'm not letting you butt
in on their date, 'kay?
[YUZU] How did everything
turn out like this?
I wanted to tell you all about
the amazing girl that I met!
Well, actually,
the person that I like
just happens to be a girl.
I saw my angel of destiny
again, isn't that great?
[SARA] I know! But even so,
you still love her, right?
[SARA]
Then do something about it!
Your heart always knows
what's best for you, Yuzu.
All you have to do is
learn to listen to it!
Look, Nina. I'm sorry.
I promised, but I can't
keep it this time.
[NINA]
Huh?
You what?
I thought you and my sister
were supposed to be friends!
[YUZU]
We are friends!
[NINA] Sara really cares
about you, Yuzu!
She would want you to be happy
if it were the other way around!
[YUZU]
I know. I feel the same way!
What's with you?
Come on!
How can you say you're friends,
and then go and do this?
[NINA]
Hm?
It's because Sara's my friend
that I know I'm doing
the right thing.
Poor Sara.
[NINA]
Wait!
What the heck are you
trying to do, Nina?
You're not giving me
any choice, Yuzu!
Ugh, don't make a scene!
If you're not gonna allow those
two to enjoy their date,
then I'm not gonna
let you leave!
Why is Sara having
a perfect date
so important to you
in the first place?
They're the ones
going out, not you!
Fine, I'll tell you why.
My sister's constantly
thinking about other people.
She's someone who puts
everyone's happiness
before her own.
Don't you see?
If you tell her that you're
in love with Mei, too,
then I just know she'll
surrender on the spot.
I love my sister, Yuzu.
And that means it's
my job to make sure
that she doesn't miss her
chance at being happy.
Sisters should always help
each other, no matter what!
Yeah, I know.
[phone ringing]
Hello, this is Yuzu.
[SARA] It's Sara.
Can we please meet up?
Uh, I need to give
you something.
Sara just called me.
She asked to meet up, and I
also wanna talk things over.
No!
This could destroy my
friendship with Sara,
and Mei might even turn me down.
But still, if I don't
confess my real feelings,
then I'm positive
I'm gonna regret it.
So please let me do
what I have to do.
[NINA]
All right.
But I'm coming, too.
[YUZU]
Sara!
Hey. Where's Mei?
There's no need to worry.
Our date's not over yet.
Although, I told her I needed
a few minutes to talk to Yuzu.
Here.
I found this at the bath,
and I couldn't help
but look at it.
So, it turns out you and
I like the same person.
Yeah. Sorry, but I'm about to--
Tell her your true feelings?
I've already said
my piece to her.
So it's only fair if
you get to do the same.
But you said
she's your destiny!
[SARA]
I know.
Even if you do confess,
I don't think she's gonna
respond the way you want.
Really? Are you sure?
Couldn't be more sure.
[chuckles]
Yeah, that's exactly what
I thought you'd say.
In the time I've spent
with Mei so far,
I've seen what a
dedicated, mature,
and wonderful person she is.
However...
She's still a scared little girl
who's trying to
protect her heart.
And you, well,
you're no different.
I think you two should try to
understand each other better.
You think we're similar?
Yep. Here ya go.
I think Mei's at the Yasaka
Shrine. Go and see her.
[YUZU]
You're staying?
[SARA] I'm not the person
she's waiting to talk to.
[YUZU]
Here.
I want you to take this.
I don't know if
it actually works,
but I hope it brings
you happiness.
[chuckles]
Wow, after all that's happened,
I'm the luckiest girl on
this whole school trip!
I'll be here to back you up!
Thanks, Sara. See ya.
What's with you? That's dumb!
I thought Mei was your--
Destiny?
So why did you--?
[SARA] I fell for Mei and
became friends with Yuzu.
Maybe my fate was to
bring those two together.
Isn't that kinda cool
to think about?
I don't think
that's cool at all!
When you talk about
that fate stuff,
it always makes me feel like
you're holding yourself back.
I can't deal with the idea of
you letting your own dreams
just slip away, okay, Sara?
Nina.
[NINA] I'm your sister.
I want the best for you.
[SARA] I'm not holding
myself back, though.
[NINA]
Huh?
Being a good friend to Yuzu,
and breaking up with Mei,
those were things I did
because I wanted to.
As for the destiny stuff,
I think I just needed it to give
me a little push, that's all.
Plus, it's more romantic
that way, right?
[NINA]
I just want to you to be happy.
[SARA] I have the best
little sister in the world.
How could I not be?
[YUZU] We should try to
understand each other better.
That's kind of like
what Matsuri said.
Here's the thing.
If you like someone, then you
have to consider their feelings.
[YUZU]
What does Mei want?
More importantly,
what does she need?
[YUZU] I've made her
the center of my world
ever since we first met.
But now that I think about it,
was that really the
best thing for Mei?
Or was I just imposing on
her by acting that way?
And then...
This'll make you happy, right?
[YUZU]
That Christmas night...
[YUZU] That's when things
got really messed up.
I love Mei.
It's not like I didn't want
to do stuff with her.
I just didn't want it
to go down like that.
Not that it's Mei's fault.
She said she needed someone
to accept her feelings,
and I wasn't able to.
Why did I act the way I did?
Maybe we're both
the problem here.
[YUZU]
Neither of us could say it,
and neither of us
were ready to hear it.
But even if that's true...
I have no choice but to confess!
[sighs]
I wasn't gonna bother you, Yuzu,
but I forgot to tell you to
bring me back a souvenir.
Uh, and I was wondering,
how are things with Mei
and your school trip going?
That works.
Eh, it's whatever.
[MATSURI] I mean, it's Yuzu.
She'll figure it out.
[HIMEKO]
Aren't we there yet?
Good news.
I've broken our schedule
into five-minute intervals.
Oh, goodie.
Wait. That's Aihara!
Ah! Excuse me, sorry!
How typical.
There's never a dull
moment with her around.
Totally. It's been crazy
since Hurricane Yuzu blew in.
But I kinda think that's what
makes her so awesome.
[sighs]
I suppose that's true.
She's made my life
interesting, for sure.
She and the president can
both get so carried away
that they can't see what's
right in front of them.
Sometimes, I'm envious of that.
Well, VP, we should
get a move on.
We've got statues to stare
at. Tons of 'em! Yay!
[YUZU]
Mei!
Please don't be gone yet!
[YUZU]
Come on!
Mei! Talk to me!
[YUZU] Oh, God. I'm so
glad I caught up to her!
This is starting
to get annoying.
I'm sorry, but there's
something I gotta say,
and I'm not letting it
go unsaid this time!
[MEI] Well, I have nothing
further to discuss with you.
[YUZU]
Uh! But!
Why can't you just listen?!
Wait up!
[YUZU] You are gonna hear me
out whether you want to or not!
So listen up, 'cause this
is happening, 'kay?
First of all, you confuse me!
One minute you're pushing
me down and kissing me,
and then you turn around and
get all clingy and fragile.
And just when I think
we're getting along,
you start acting like
you hate my guts!
Nothing you do makes
any sense to me!
[YUZU] But despite all that, you
have feelings for me, don't you?
[gasps]
[YUZU]
That Christmas night...
My heart was
racing for you, Mei.
Being that close to you
made me so happy.
I wasn't thinking of
your feelings, though,
so I couldn't accept them!
And then, the night
your dad came home,
I felt horrible, and I
agonized over it forever,
but I didn't do
anything to fix it!
I don't wanna go through any
of that stuff again, okay?
The truth is,
I'm in love with you.
And I can promise you,
I will need you.
Always.
So, if maybe you feel the
same way that I do, then...
[YUZU]
...would you please kiss me?
Thanks.
But... I want one from you.
[NINA]
Hm?
Hey!
Sara, look! Yuzu
and Mei are here!
[giggles]
[SARA]
How 'bout that?
Looks like they didn't need
backup from me after all.
Oh, you helped
more than you think.
[YUZU] Hey, I'm sorry for
making you guys wait so long.
Oh, no. Don't worry about that.
There's still a little more time
before we have to go back home.
[YUZU] Listen, before
we do anything else,
I was hoping that Mei and I
could have a quick
talk with you.
I know we've caused a
lot of trouble lately,
and we just wanted to apologize.
No, it's okay.
Uh, let's find a store then.
[NINA]
Hey.
You know somethin'? I'm hungry!
What do you say, Yuzu?
Wanna go grab a snack with me?
Huh? Like, now?
I wanna pay you back
for your kindness, okay?
[YUZU] Uh, it's no big
deal or anything--
No, don't be silly. I insist!
I'll tell you all of Sara's
embarrassing secrets.
So come on, it'll be fun!
Off we go!
[YUZU]
Help! Stranger danger!
[SARA]
I feel kinda bad for Yuzu.
But I figured I should
talk to you one-on-one.
Pretty good timing.
So, tell me,
were you able to find out
what your true feelings are?
I'm sorry.
[SARA]
Huh?
What are you sorry for?
[MEI] You've been nothing
but kind to me.
And I have nothing
to offer in return.
If there's any way to
make it up to you...
[SARA]
Mei!
That's enough. Stop being
so hard on yourself.
Even if your intentions
are honorable,
no matter what, the
only way I'll be happy
is if you get to be happy, too.
You could stand to be a
whole lot more selfish.
All right. I will say I
don't want to lose you.
[SARA chuckles]
Good.
Well then, I know how
to ease your mind.
I'll let you do me
a little favor!
[SARA] Okay, it's about
time for us to go home!
We should all go to Kyoto
again one day soon!
Just us four!
That sounds awesome!
I'll call ya soon!
Cool! Looking forward to it!
See ya! Have a safe trip!
Those two, you think
we'll see 'em again?
Of course.
Yuzu?
[YUZU]
Hm?
[YUZU gasps]
You know that's my hand, right?
I'm aware. We should head back.
What's happening?
This is so crazy!
She started it and everything!
It's freezing outside,
but I feel so warm!
Don't be ridiculous.
[chuckles]
So, Sara, what'd you
talk about with Mei?
I made a little deal with her.
I said if she holds Yuzu's
hand, she's forgiven! Ha!
[NINA]
Here! I'll hold yours!
Sure.
[NINA giggles]
So, the fact that you kissed me
after I said all that stuff...
...does that mean you're,
you know, in love with me, too?
I don't know. We'll see
if dating works out.
[YUZU] Jeez. Can't you
say yes or no for once?
Uh.
Um, wait.
Did you just say that
we were dating?
[YUZU] Up till now, I had
never been in love before.
Can I ask something?
[YUZU]
I'm beyond clueless about love.
Or at least, that's
what I used to think.
Could we kiss one more time?
[YUZU humming]
All done!
Here you go, girls. Take care!
Thanks, Mom! See ya!
[MEI]
We'll be going now, Mother.
[HIMEKO]
President!
Great! She's here, too!
[HIMEKO growling]
Himeko, good morning.
A pleasure as
always, President.
The gang's all here!
--Hey, Harumin.
--Greetings, Taniguchi.
[YUZU] Mei and I are
still trying to figure out
how to be stepsisters.
I'm not sure what destiny has
in store, but for now...
Yuzu.