-All right, get back.
GIRL IN CROWD 1:
Why all of a sudden
is Senri looking
so manly lately?
GIRL IN CROWD 2:
Hey, Senri is mine.
-OK, everyone, don't push. it;s
past curfew for the day class
students.
-Move it, disciplinary
committee.
-Senri.
-I guess I really can't
handle them all by myself.
All by myself.
-Good evening, ladies.
Did any of you dream
about me last night?
[screams]
-Yikes.
-Wonderful.
So then tonight I shall
make a little detour
and invade Yuki Cross's dreams.
You're it.
GIRL IN CROWD: Hey,
why'd you pick Yuki?
-Wait a minute, Hanabusa--
I'm so sorry, Kana--
-Exactly what are
you doing, Yuki?
GIRL IN CROWD: Oh
no, Zero's back.
Things were more peaceful
when he was away.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): There are
so many things I want to say.
-Uh.
um.
-So many things I
want to talk about.
How is your wound?
All that time I didn't see
you, what was going on?
And have you found a way to
satisfy your thirst for blood?
-All right, enough.
Now go back to your dorms.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): There's
so much I want to ask.
The words are almost
spilling out of me.
But--
[crowd complaining]
-Zero, welcome back.
-Yeah, thank you.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): Kaname Kuran.
[theme music]
-Ah, what's with this
invade your dreams?
Ridiculous.
-Well, if you appeared,
it would be a nightmare.
-What was that?
-You know, I admire that
about you, Hanabusa.
-And just what does that mean?
-You always manage to
play your role perfectly,
and I'm sure that's
no easy task.
-Listen, everyone, will
you all do me a favor?
ALL: With pleasure, Lord Kaname.
-Lord Kaname, are you sure?
-Snip, snip.
Hm, beautiful.
Oh, why, hello.
You only had the day
class to teach today?
-Ya.
I see Zero is back now.
-I guess you would notice that.
Zero was in a terrible
state when he left.
I still don't know how he was
able to regain his sanity.
-Well, I'm not the renowned
hunter that you are.
There's lots of
things I tend to miss.
However, I'd able to spot
an apron as ugly as that
from a mile away.
-Huh?
This is cute.
-I'm so sorry, Kana--
ZERO (VOICEOVER): That guy's
blood is coursing through me.
Can Yuki sense it?
Kaname Kuran.
Ever since I drank his
blood, this vision I
have of that-- that monster.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Zero.
Shizuka Hio was
here at the Academy.
In order for Zero to stop his
inevitable fall into a level E,
he had to drink the
blood of that woman who
dealt him such a cruel fate.
And yet, I doubt that Zero
was able to drink her blood.
I wonder how much time
Zero has left now?
If drinking my blood would
slow his fall to a level E,
I'd let him have as
much as he wanted.
-Why do you insist
on doing this?
You don't need to
care for me so much.
-Zero.
-I only wanted to protect you.
-Kaname, I--
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Don't
tell me that in the end
I can't do anything without
Zero and Kaname protecting me.
Zero.
There's one thing I can do.
-Zero!
For a whole week, I
had to work really hard
and do this job all
by myself, you know.
You had better work
twice as hard tonight.
-You can be so--
-Come on, now, aren't
you craving it?
I mean, I'm sure
they didn't give you
any at the medical
clinic, right?
So just for tonight, I'm willing
to give you an extra helping.
-Don't be stupid.
-Zero.
Zero.
I'm sorry.
Listen, I've said this before,
but I-- I am on your side.
I may not be much help.
Actually, I'm pretty
useless, and I really
hate that about myself.
I wanted you to drink
her blood so badly,
I'd have forced you to drink it.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): It was
the only way to save Zero,
and all I've done is
cause him more suffering.
-I'm so sorry.
-Just what am I to you, Yuki?
-What are you to me?
-Stop.
No more reckless acts
on my behalf, OK?
Am I that hopeless?
-Oh, this is serious,
serious news.
-What is it, Headmaster?
-She's awake.
Maria Kurenai has woken up.
-Maria is awake now?
-It's Ichiro.
You lied, Headmaster.
He is to here.
-Well, that one is--
-Ichiru, that man is so cruel.
He says Shizuka was
killed-- you're not-- are
you-- are you really Zero?
-Maria.
-So Shizuka actually
did meet you then.
So must-- she must
really be dead.
At Shizuka's request,
I lent her my body
from time to time
when see needed it.
In return, Shizuka promised
to make me healthy.
But since I'm related
to her by blood,
I still would have even
without any promises.
Shizuka was put in isolation
right after she was born.
They said it was to protect
her, but no one ever
loved or even cared for her.
The one Shizuka cared for was
the first person in her life
who ever showed her any
form of love at all,
and when she lost him,
all her sadness and anger
caused her to go insane.
Zero, listen, I don't think
she regretted you killing her.
-All right.
Calm down, Maria.
You've only just woken up.
-No, Maria, that isn't what--
-It's OK, Yuki.
Let's let her rest for now.
Zero.
-Wait.
Zero, I want to make sure that
at least tell you the truth.
-What?
-You see, the Kiryus
were used as pawns
when they hunted
Shizuka's lover.
There was someone else
behind the scenes.
Someone who was not
happy that she was in
love with a vampire,
who used to be a human.
When Shizuka realized
who the real culprit was,
she attempted to gain more
power to destroy her enemy.
Whoever did these things
to her is the real enemy,
the enemy of the
purebloods and of you.
-A true enemy.
-Maria also believes
that Zero killed Shizuka.
But, at that time,
Zero was-- I thought
that I saw someone here.
-Good evening, miss.
This is Cross Academy, isn't it?
I apologize for visiting
at such a late hour,
but I'm afraid that I lost
track of time at the office.
-I can sense it.
You're-- you're a vampire.
-I am, and the young
lady is a guardian.
I was wondering something.
-Just what do you want?
-Where is the other guardian?
-Zero.
-What do you want with me?
-Zero Kiryu, the Senate,
the highest governing body
of vampires, has
issued an order,
and I'm here to execute you for
the murder of the pure blood
vampire Shizuka Hio.
You see, the Senate proudly
protects our pureblood masters,
and yet, somehow you slipped
through and killed Shizuka.
-Wait!
Zero didn't--
-Stop!
The only way you can
atone for your sin is
to offer your life in return,
a cheapest price to pay,
isn't it?
Yah!
You have a lot of
nerve breaking my hand.
Soon, you'll just be
another vile level E.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): My
strength has increased.
-Zero.
-Sorry, but I'm not
willing to pay that price.
-Even if you kill me, you
can't escape your fate.
You will be executed
for your crime.
-Go on.
This has nothing to do with you.
-I won't do that.
-It was inevitable for
Shizuka to be hunted down
by Zero for what she did.
-Lord Kaname.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
Hunted down by Zero?
-Tell me, why do you
all feel so strongly
about Zero's execution?
To protect the so-called
sanctity of purebloods.
-Lord Kaname, if a
pureblood, such as yourself,
stands in our way, we
cannot complete our mission.
-Perhaps you don't realize this
Academy is very dear to me.
I don't want it spoiled by
foolish acts of vengeance
performed by the
Senate's henchmen.
-Lord Kaname, please.
Ah!
-Leave now.
-You're choice to protect Zero
Kiryu shall be reporting back
to the Senate, Lord Kaname.
-Are you all right?
-So Kaname, why'd you save me?
-Because I simply
will not tolerate
the execution of a school
mate by foolish members
of my race for
groundless reasons.
-Zero.
Thank you very much.
-It's fine.
-No, thank you.
But still, there's
absolutely no reason
why Zero should be
targeted for this.
-Yes, I know that.
Don't worry.
-No.
You don't understand.
How dare you speak that way to--
-Now, now.
All right, everyone,
it's time you all
go back to the classroom.
-But Lord Kaname was--
-Let's go.
-Just what is it that
I don't understand?
-That Shizuka was
hunted by Zero.
It wasn't him.
he didn't have
anything to do with it.
-Yuki, I have no intention
of making Zero a villain.
Please, belief that.
-Then say it.
I want you to say you realize
that Zero isn't the killer.
-Sure.
If you say it's true,
then I concede it.
-Come on, I'm serious.
-And I have always
been serious about you.
-Zero is not the guilty one.
-This talk is going
nowhere, Yuki.
-I don't care if
it goes nowhere.
Until you say Zero is
innocent, then I-- then
I won't ever speak to you again.
--[chuckling] This isn't a
children's quarrel here.
Uh, very sorry.
-He's willing to defy the
Senate to protect Cross Academy.
Just what is Lord
Kaname thinking?
-Does it really matter
what he's thinking?
-What are you saying, Senri?
-It really doesn't matter
what he's thinking.
We will simply obey
without question.
Personally, I find it
quite comfortable here.
-Senri, since President Kuran
created this place for us.
-I agree with what Senri said.
-Me too.
He's right.
The night class will
stand with Lord Kaname.
-And so will I, completely.
-What's wrong?
-Sorry, did I wake you?
-You can't sleep?
-I was just thinking about
how childish I can be.
-That's true.
But I don't think that your
childish side is actually
a weakness, Yuki.
Goodnight.
-Thanks, Juri.
-What do you want?
-You did it.
It was you who killed Shizuka
after I had already shot her.
I've heard the flesh
and blood of purebloods
hold strong powers.
So her powers, you took them?
-You heard?
As if you have no idea.
You know.
You know first hand.
You realize my blood
won't save you forever.
It's only temporary.
I pity you Zero.
But at the same
time, I'm envious you
can protect the girl you like.
-You and I are not done talking.
I spoke to Maria, who
is this real enemy
of the purebloods
she told me about?
-There's no need for
you to know that.
-You
-I just realized there's
another way of looking at this.
The only reason you
can protect Yuki
is because my blood
is flowing inside you.
I know you think that you're
the one protecting Yuki,
but really, it's me.
-You bastard.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): Kaname
Kuran's blood lives inside me.
-Come on now.
Aren't you craving it?
Kaname Kuran's blood should
have satisfied me for a while,
but still all I want is Yuki.
-You wanted to kill me
all this time, Zero Kiryu.
Where will your desires
go now that you've
lost your reason to live?
Will it be replaced by the--
-Merciless instincts
of a vampire?
ZERO (VOICEOVER): Blood.
The overwhelming
sweet smell of blood.
-Yuki!
-Zero?
What is it?
-Yuki.
you're alive.
-Zero.
-I thought I'd killed you.
-You're hurting me, Zero.
Zero, are you all right?
-Yeah.
-Thank goodness.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): I want this.
I want her gentle hands.
Her smile.
-It's nothing.
-The Senate sent
men to the Academy?
-They did.
-What's the Hunter
Association doing?
No matter how you
look at it, they--
-From the Hunter Association,
and it's addressed to Zero.
[theme music]