-Calling you my nephew kind
of gives me the creeps.
The last time we met was a
little over 10 years ago,
right?
You hurt me, Kaname.
That day, you shattered my
body until I lost my shape.
It took 10 years
to regain my form.
Well, I suppose I should
thank my pureblood power which
allowed me to survive.
Oh, by the way, thank you
so much for getting rid
of my fiance, Shizuka.
It was a load off my mind.
If I waited around for
her to become obedient
like his mother, I'm
fairly certain that I
would have waited for
close to an eternity.
I'm glad to see
-That you haven't
changed, Uncle.
You are still someone
that I want to kill,
and I would never feel the
slightest bit of remorse
for it.
-No.
Kaname, stop.
I'm sorry, but I won't
let you hurt Senri.
I cannot stand by and allow him
to be sacrificed in the battle
between the two of you?
-So then, should I take
that to mean your allegiance
lies with the Senate on this?
-Well, you could
interpret it that way.
-I see.
-Kaname can't kill
me, even if he wanted.
Now, for the time being,
I'm going to use his room.
I'm counting on you,
Dorm President Kuran.
[theme music]
[murmuring]
-So you couldn't sleep again?
-Yeah, but really I'm all right.
It's just a lack of
sleep, that's all.
-What is-- hey, Akatsuki.
-Yeah, what?
-See that?
AKATSUKI: Senri?
When'd he get back?
And is he with--
HANABUSA: Ichiru Kiryu.
-Wonder what that's all about.
Rima, do you know--
-I don't.
-His lover?
Kaname Kuran's?
-Yes.
-Interesting.
So that's why they've all
agreed to be her bodyguard.
And where's my vial?
-I'm afraid it has been lost.
-You're not very
useful, are you?
-No matter.
It's almost time anyway.
Even if we leave her
alone, that girl eventually
will-- however there's
still work to do.
Do your job well,
and I'll make sure
that your little
wish is fulfilled.
-Yes, you will
kill those who are
responsible for Shizuka's death.
Therefore, from the
very bottom of my heart,
I wish for your real body to be
resurrected, Lord Rido Kuran.
-So tell me, Yuki,
how are things
going between you and Kaname?
-I don't have any idea
what you're talking about.
[gasping]
-Oh no, don't cry.
I understand how upsetting
it is that Kaname chose Yuki,
but (SOBBING) we should
be happy for them!
[crying]
-Troublesome.
-So you still finding ways to
be involved with the Senate?
-That's really none of
your business, is it?
-Listen, if something
happens to Yuki,
you'll see a
different side of me.
-So scary.
-Once every 10 years.
-Is something wrong?
-Yuki?
-Hey, Akatsuki!
-Senri, what's wrong?
Where have you been
this whole time?
-Aren't you bored, cooped
up in here all by yourself?
-Senri, what have you--
-I have so much time
on my hands right now.
What do you say?
Let's have a little
fun together.
-Stop joking.
-Oh, I wasn't making a joke.
I'm serious.
-Let me go, Senri.
-Oh, sorry.
You see, I don't have total
control over my power yet.
Did that hurt?
If so, I'll try my best
to be gentle next time.
-Akatsuki!
-Senri, you bastard.
What were you doing?
-It's pretty obvious.
-Akatsuki, what are you--
-Stop!
Senri, go back to your room.
-So you're ordering
me around now?
-What have you--
-Just who do you think
you're talking to?
-I'm sorry.
Just please, go on
back to your room.
-Well, seeing how you
asked nicely this time.
See you around.
-Ruka, are you all right?
-Yes.
Takuma, what's wrong with Senri?
-Why don't you let me try
and deal with him for now.
And please, don't say
anything to Kaname.
-To Lord Kaname.
-But he--
-Akatsuki.
-Fine.
As you wish.
-OK, Ruka?
-Yes.
-I really am sorry
about all this.
-Akatsuki, thank you.
-Oh, man.
What is going on around here?
-It's no fun always meeting
up on school grounds.
Should we go somewhere tomorrow?
-Kaname, listen, I--
-What's wrong?
-Kaname, you still haven't--
you still haven't answered
my question.
-About what?
-I want to know if-- if
somehow or another you
are connected to my past.
Hanabusa told me something.
He said the only
reason you-- you
made me your lover
was because it
was the best way for
you to protect me.
As if there's
something-- what are
you trying to protect me from?
Is something going
to happen to me?
And does this mean when
you said those words to me,
when you said "I love you"--
come on, Kaname, please.
Please answer my question.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
So much blood.
-Yuki, I saw a rare rose that
blooms once every 10 years.
It's a rose encased in resin.
These roses bloom only
once every 10 years.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): No!
JURI (VOICEOVER):
There's only one truth.
-Yuki.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
Help.
Help me!
JURI (VOICEOVER):
You cannot run away.
There's nowhere to run.
-I just-- I just want--
-Yuki, calm down.
Yuki--
YUKI (VOICEOVER): No!
JURI (VOICEOVER): You can't run.
You can't run.
-What's happening?
I don't understand
what's happening.
Who are you to me?
How are we connected?
And why do you go to
such lengths to hide it?
Tell me what happened
to me, Kaname.
I just-- I just want to
know what the truth is.
-Yuki, Yuki--
-Kana-- Kaname-- tell me, why
is it that when you look at me,
your eyes are so sad?
-It's all right.
I will protect you.
I promise.
-Yuki, it seems that
finally the time has come.
Juri.
I only hope I have the
strength to protect her.
-Senri?
-Dorm President is
trying to protect
Yuki Cross from something.
-Ichiru's transfer, then
Takuma, and now Senri.
-That guy--
-Those eyes.
Is that really Senri?
-Both of you have had some
really bad experiences
in your life-- I mean, horrible.
So the last thing I want--
-Wake up.
Wake up and give your
blood to the monster
who sleeps in this casket.
-It's almost time.
Very soon, it will
be in my possession.
And when it is, I will then
make a full resurrection.
As you know, when that child
awakens from her slumber,
her sweet dreams will
then turn into nightmares.
And her ferocious
fangs will start
destroying her from the inside.
And I won't even have
to lift a finger.
She'll wake up no
matter what I do.
And then, with her blood--
-Rido, don't delude
yourself for even a second.
Your filthy hands
will never touch her.
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
It's all right, Yuki.
All that I ask is that
you just be yourself.
-No!
No!
-Yuki, are you awake?
-Ze-- ro?
-Are you all right?
-Why-- why aren't
you fighting back?
-Yuki, I told you, you can do
whatever you want with my life.
-Because you think that
I'm your victim, Zero?
-You're wrong.
You're so naive.
Can't you see that I'm the
one you can never escape from,
Zero?
I'm the one who's forced you to
play along with my selfishness.
All this time, me
being your only ally,
doing everything I could
possibly do for you.
I was only doing those
things for myself.
I thought if I could pretend
I was indispensable to you,
then it wouldn't matter if
I didn't have my own past.
Yes, I did it all for myself.
Otherwise--
-Do you think my heart will grow
stronger if I become a vampire?
--I would've never
said something
that I really shouldn't have.
ZERO: Yuki, you're
not making any sense.
It sounds as if
you're desperately
saying that you
really do need me.
But you're wrong, Yuki.
The only one you really
need is Kaname Kuran,
and it has been that way
from the very beginning.
Something is wrong with you.
-(CHUCKLING) I'm sorry, Zero.
-You really all right?
-I've been hallucinating,
and it makes me act weird.
I'm really sorry.
You should leave now.
I need to change out
of this nightgown, OK?
-Are you sure you're all right?
-Yes, I promise you
I'm perfectly fine.
Thank you.
Bye.
[sobbing]
ZERO: Kaname, I
want to know what
you intend to do with Yuki.
-You will not betray her.
-Red snow.
The world is dyed in blood,
and I can't see anything else.
I tried.
I tried my best to remember.
-Yuki, stop.
That's enough.
It's time that you wake
up before you go mad.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): It's cold,
but somehow I feel warm.
-Kaname, what are you-- Kaname,
what is buried in my neck?
-Yuki.
Please, only you.
-What the--
-This is--
-That blood smells
like-- but it can't be.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): This
taste, it's Kaname's blood.
Have you woken, Yuki?
Do you remember who I am?
-You're my--
ZERO: I know that smell.
It's Yuki's blood.
However--
-Zero--
-Now I sense two vampires.
Kaname, you've turned Yuki.
-No, stop it, Zero.
This man, he's-- he's
my-- my older brother.
I'm-- I'm so sorry, Zero.
-You're-- siblings?
-That's right.
However, if I were truly
born her older brother,
then I would have
been much happier.
[theme music]