[intro music playing]
[piano music playing]
ZERO (VOICEOVER): Sorry.
It's nothing.
I'm not myself.
Just woke up from a nightmare.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
I'm sure that's it.
I mean, Zero's been
through so much lately.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): So much.
YUKI: Until you see
Zero is innocent,
then I-- I won't ever
speak to you again!
(GROANING)
-What's going on with you, Yuki?
-Oh!
It's nothing!
We better hurry before
they lock the gate!
Huh?
-(CRYING) Mommy!
YUKI: You lost?
Did you lose your mommy?
-(CRYING) Take me to my mommy!
-Hey, Yori, I'm going to help
this boy find his mother.
Can you head back to
the dorm without me?
-Will you be OK by yourself?
-I'll be perfectly fine.
So, shall we go?
KAIEN: Here.
It's a written order
from the Association.
You are to monitor
tonight's Vampire Soiree.
It's being held nearby.
I don't foresee any problems.
It's a gathering of
moderates, so there
shouldn't be any trouble.
-Got it.
I understand.
[door opening and closing]
[theme music playing]
YUKI: We're a long
way from the market.
Are you sure we're
going the right way?
CHILD: M'hm.
[bell ringing]
RIMA: Senri, aren't
you ready yet?
-This is so annoying.
I hate gatherings that
are filled with grownups.
-Well, it can't be avoided.
Just put up with it
for a little while.
-Oh.
-Hanabusa, the Aido family is
the one putting on this event
tonight.
MOTHER: And your
father is coming, too,
so try to cheer up a little bit.
-That is why I'm not keen on it.
ICHIJOU: I've
decided that we shall
overlook yesterday's
disturbance.
Zero Kiryu will not to
be dealt with as long
as you are at Cross
Academy, Lord Kaname.
-I do appreciate that, Ichijou.
ICHIJOU: I must admit, I find
the fair and impartial way
you vouch and defend
your schoolmate
to be quite admirable.
Fitting behavior for the
head of the Kuran family
who paved the way for the
pacifism we practice today.
-Actually, Ichijou, I
would like for the Senate
to grant me a specific request.
Going forward, I ask
you not to interfere
with the affairs
at Cross Academy.
Like my late
parents before me, I
have no desire to be a
part of anymore bloodshed.
-Huh?
Is this really the place?
CHILD: Hm.
Thank you so much, miss.
I was afraid all by myself.
-Well, I really don't
want to leave you alone,
so I'll stay until
your mom comes.
-Thanks a lot.
you're very kind, miss.
-Huh?
-What?
-This--
-Thank you.
-Hanbusa.
-What is it, Akatsuki?
-For some reason, Yuki Cross
is lying here unconscious.
-Huh?
-Troublesome girl.
[gasping]
-Where am I?
-Huh?
-What a relief.
You managed to come
to rather quickly.
-Kaname!
I'm really not-- I'm not
sure how this happened!
-Yuki.
-Thank you.
KANAME: I thought that you
weren't speaking to me.
-Um-- I, I just meant that if
you would stop suspecting Zero,
then I--
KANAME: I've already told you.
I have no intention of
turning Zero into a criminal.
However, until we know for
sure who the real murderer is,
Zero is someone
I can't rule out.
YUKI: Well, I
understand that, but--
-One more thing, Yuki.
When I heard you say
that to me, did you
think it wouldn't anger me?
-Yes, but you have to
remember it was your fault
I said that, Kaname.
-Don't you know you
made me act that way?
KANAME: I sensed your
heart skip a beat,
so clearly you do
understand a little.
[knocking]
KANAME: All right.
Come in.
-You're here, too, Takuma?
-Yuki, you're awake.
Thank goodness.
You gave me quite
a scary, seeing
you lying there in the entryway.
What happened to you?
-I'm not sure.
I took a lost child to what
looked like an abandoned
building.
He kissed my cheek to
thank me, and then--
-Well, he was most likely a
child of one of the guests.
You see, a vampire child can
suck in your life energy.
You're in an
underground mansion that
was built beneath an
abandoned building.
This place belongs
to the Aido family.
And tonight, there's
a soiree for vampires
who live in this vicinity.
[music playing]
TAKUMA: There are many
aristocrats here right now.
-I must admit.
I didn't expect to see
Ichijou at this event.
-Yeah, I know.
That is a bit of a rare sight.
Hanabusa, I wouldn't
let him bother you.
-And look, a soiree like this
is being observed by a hunter.
It's an agreement so
the two sides get along.
HANABUSA: But why did they
send him of all people?
ZERO: Cut it out, Master.
-Hello, dumb pupil.
-Why did you come here tonight?
-Because I got an order, too.
-I don't need your
help, you know.
I can handle this on my own.
Will you quit touching me?
-Huh.
I have such a heartless pupil.
KAIEN: You didn't get an order.
Don't worry.
The vampires who are
gathering at this event
are empathetic as they wish
to coexist with humans.
-Your instincts are
completely out of touch.
Do you honestly mean to
just sit here in that chair,
and watch from the sidelines?
Huh, Kaien Cross?
MAN: Ichijou's here.
Why would an old Senate member
come to something like this?
WOMAN: It must be
because of that incident.
-Empathetic vampires, huh?
KANAME: Listen.
Under no circumstances
are you to leave this room
until I return.
I will go and notify
the Headmaster.
Do not leave this room, Yuki.
-A room without widows.
It's strange.
I feel like I've been in
a room like this before.
-Huh?
What was--
[door opening]
-I'm sorry for what I did
to you earlier, Miss Human.
-So it turns out that
you're a vampire, huh?
Did you find your mother?
Hey!
Hold on!
Is this--
[music playing]
-A light?
-I knew it.
I really shouldn't have come.
-Senri.
I haven't seen you
in a long time.
My, how you've grown.
You're a fine young man now.
-It's so nice to see
you, Great Uncle.
-But, you do seem a
little on the thin side.
It's important
that you eat well.
Keep in mind that this
body is not yours alone.
When you get a chance,
you should go and visit
your mother.
Bye Senri.
[chime]
[gasping]
-A ballroom full of vampires.
Actors and musicians
who won famous awards.
The president of a
software company?
They're all vampires?
[gasping]
-Why?
Why is he--
-Why is Zero--
[people laughing and talking]
-Why is Zero here?
He couldn't have been invited.
He must be working.
He must be here to
monitor this gathering.
Zero is acting like he
usually does, unlike me.
I see.
-Why do I keep
thinking about that?
Stop it!
[organ music playing]
-Excuse me.
I didn't mean to
interrupt everyone.
Please enjoy yourselves.
-Lord Kaname.
Is what we heard true?
Did you stand up against the
Senate to defend a human?
-I did.
-I respectable Lord Kaname.
WOMAN: You must
believe it's time
we meet the human half way.
For both our futures.
MAN: What a noble cause.
-Lord Kaname.
Thank you for putting
up with my son.
-Thank you for inviting
me tonight, Lord Aido.
I'm not comfortable
at soirees, so it
seems that I hardly
ever attend them.
-Please.
Don't worry about it.
If I could impose on you,
we have a special favor
to ask you tonight.
Tsukiko.
-Father, no!
-I would like to introduce
you to my daughter, Tsukiko.
She's a lovely girl.
It's the hope of our
entire clan that you
take a fancy to
her, Lord Kaname.
-Father, please.
I'm sorry, Lord Kaname!
That's not my wish.
KANAME: I don't know what
will happen in the future,
but I will remember her.
MAN: Lord Kaname, please
come meet my daughter.
MAN: I'd like you to
meet my daughter, too.
WOMAN: And my daughter.
Lord Kaname.
My daughter is so fond of you.
She'll do anything you ask.
WOMAN: Lord Kaname has changed.
In the past, he used to
ignore this topic completely.
WOMAN: Indeed.
He has matured.
He now understands his
role as a rare Pureblood.
[organ music playing]
-Ichiru?
-It seems that everybody
is very surprised.
They all can't
believe that you're
attending this
soiree, Grandfather.
Is something the matter?
-Not at all.
I was just thinking
of something trivial.
Death will come calling
to the person who
sees their other self.
(LAUGHS) A silly myth
passed on by the humans.
-Hello, Zero.
-Why would you want to come
to something like this?
-You're looking well.
I have to say, I
thought by now you
would've fallen to a Level E.
-Ichiru.
We're leaving.
Make sure you see Ichijou home.
-Of course.
-Ichiru, what are you--
-I'm employed by the Senate now.
So chances are the two of us
will meet again somewhere.
Oh, and Zero, have you heard
of the curse of the twins?
-What are you saying?
-(LAUGHING) I guess you haven't.
Never mind the.
-I knew he was way
beyond my reach.
But still, I wish
I hadn't seen that.
[door opening]
KANAME: May I come in?
-Sure
-I told you not to leave
this room, didn't I?
-Um, I'm sorry.
-No.
This time, Yuki, an
apology is not enough.
[gasping]
-Why'd you go out?
-That child.
I just wanted to see if
he had found his mom.
MOM: Let's go home.
-OK!
I'm coming, mommy!
-So, Ichiru.
Just don't do anything stupid.
You don't want to make that
little disciplinary committee
member worry.
-She is not little.
Her very existence
means the world to me.
[piano music playing]
-Kaname, are you--
-Until I forgive
you, stay with me
a little longer just like this.
I'm so tired.
-Yes, of course.
I'll do anything for
you, Lord Kaname.
YUKI: I love you, Lord Kaname.
My world began with you.
So even if my past is
empty, I'm not afraid.
-Yuki.
-I had told myself that I
would no longer call you
Lord Kaname like I used to.
But I'm not silly little
girl anymore, though.
I know you're way
out of my reach.
That's what I told myself.
And I tried.
I thought if I didn't
forget all you'd
done for me, that
it would be enough.
But I still--
[gasping]
-Kaname, what are you--
KANAME: Humans are
fleeting beings.
Their lives rushing through what
is only a moment for vampires.
Will you become a vampire?
Will you become a monster
that devours blood?
And live the long flow
of time with me, Yuki?
-I will.
-Sorry.
I took this too far.
I won't do anything.
-I apologize for
frightening you.
-Kaname, I-- I
thought that you--
-Come now.
What's with that face?
I hope you've
learned your lesson.
Don't get yourself into
dangerous situations anymore.
All right?
Your ride home should
be here by now.
-Welcome back, Yuki.
-Thank you.
I'm sorry that I made you wait.
-It's snowing.
-White snow.
Reminds me of red blood.
That snow ten years ago
splattered with blood.
The beautiful boy who extended
his bloodstained hand to me,
and I held it.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): As long
as Lord Kaname is with me,
there's nothing
that I'm afraid of.
I can do anything for him.
-And live the long flow
of time with me, Yuki.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
Somewhere in my heart,
I had been longing
to hear those words.
I never thought I
would hear them.
So I got all confused, and
my feelings turned to tears.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
What you asked of me,
Kaname, even if you weren't
serious-- did my reaction let
you down?
[students talking loudly]
GIRL: The holiday
starts tomorrow!
We won't be able to
see Aido for so long!
I'm going to miss you so much!
-Ruka!
There is a fire in my heart
that I absolutely must--
ZERO: Shut up!
-Zero!
-Why don't you quit daydreaming
and actually do your job?
-Sorry.
[students screaming]
-All right, everyone!
Get back!
-Ruka!
Ruka!
-I hope you do realize, Yuki.
I know what you told
me was the truth.
So please, stop worrying.
BOY: Ruka!
[credit music playing]