[music playing]
[door creaks]
BUTLER: Welcome.
-Hey there, Great-Uncle.
-Thanks for coming, Senri.
Come right this way.
[door closes heavily]
I want to show you something.
SENRI: I don't like this.
What is it?
HARUKA: You're no
longer a child.
So as a member of
the Shiki family,
you have a duty to
know-- the secret
I have worked so
hard to conceal.
I've been protecting you.
Take a look.
This is your father.
[music - on/off, "rinne rondo"]
SENRI: I thought he was dead.
This is gross.
RIDO: How could you say that
to your own flesh and blood?
I've managed to
regenerate quite a bit.
I was looking forward to
seeing you all grown up.
-I'm sorry to keep
you waiting, my lord.
-Oh!
[splash]
RIDO: My dear son, Senri.
I am in need of your strength.
-Uh!
HANABUSA: Hm, now which
one should I choose?
Ah, this one.
-Uh?
Mm, again.
-You're too easy to read, Rima.
-Old Maid is so boring
with just two people.
Senri should have come, too.
-You want him to come because
you can always beat him.
-That's not the only reason.
I wonder how he's doing,
if he's all right at home.
-Hm?
SEIREN: My lord, he
has made his move.
-Yes, I know that.
He should have stayed asleep.
-Uh?
-I'm going back.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Do you think
my heart will grow stronger
if I become a vampire?
What I said was terrible.
Zero has been struggling so
hard since becoming a vampire.
Everyone has left, gone
back to their homes,
to their real parents.
Somewhere in my heart,
there's an uneasiness
that comes when I try
to remember my past.
Did my parents abandon me?
Who am I, really?
CROSS: Oh, Yuki.
Dinner's going to be
ready in a minute,
so go take a bath
now if you want.
-Mm.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
I wonder when I
stopped having those
terrifying nights.
That's right-- after Zero
came to live with us.
His suffering made me feel
like I had to do something.
I was so desperate to help.
But I had no idea what Zero
was really suffering from.
-I will never left
that happen to you.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Instead
of protecting him,
I've been hurting him
with my insecurities.
I must remember so I
don't keep hurting Zero.
I must remember!
[gasp]
ZERO: Yuki, you've been
in that bath a long time,
so the headmaster wanted
me to check on you.
You all right?
-Uh, y-yeah.
[gasp]
[screams]
-Yuki!
What is it?
[breathing shakily]
YUKI: I-- I just saw blood.
[pounding on door]
ZERO: Hey, Yuki.
Are you OK?
YUKI: It was nothing.
I'm getting out now.
-All right, then.
I'll see you at dinner, OK?
YUKI: Please, stay
here for a while.
ZERO: What's wrong?
YUKI: I tried to
remember my past.
But then--
-You were left.
You were just abandoned in
a desolate location where
vampires are known
to roam, right?
If your parents were
vampire hunters or connected
to the Vampire
Hunter Association,
what you're thinking
would make sense.
YUKI: But the headmaster said
there was no such incident.
-The association's records.
Perhaps if you
read them yourself,
you might find something new.
What do you think?
CROSS: Are you sure you
two really want to do this?
I can't recommend
visiting that place.
-Zero, listen to him.
Is it OK for us to go there?
-Don't you want to see
things with your own eyes?
-Mm.
-To be honest, I'm more
worried about Zero right now
than you, Yuki.
His current situation
is rather delicate, so--
ZERO: They won't kill me the
second I walk in the door
just because I'm a vampire now.
-That's true, but--
-Besides, what are you two doing
following us around, anyway?
This isn't some
parent-teacher conference.
-We're just worried because
it's only the two of you, right?
-Hm.
-So what is the real
reason you're here today?
-I just came to
snoop around, see
what the association is up to.
I hate this town.
You have no idea who's
eavesdropping on you here.
CROSS: Yes.
All the residents of
this town are either
vampire hunters or those
working for the association.
This is the headquarters of the
Vampire Hunters' Association.
-Uh?
-It's not you that
they're staring at.
-Mm.
I don't like this atmosphere.
YAGARI: Later.
-But Mr. Yagari, where are you--
-Perhaps he has a girlfriend
that he would like to see.
ZERO: Doubtful.
VAMPIRE HUNTER: Hmph.
There should be a spell on this
building to repel vampires.
Guess that means you've
already been tamed, huh?
Ah, I can see your tattoo.
-Now just hold on, mister!
You think it's all
right for you to bully
someone younger than you?
-Oh, so this brat's
your master, huh?
-Did you just call me a brat?
PRESIDENT: That's enough, now.
Zero is indeed our ally.
He was born into the
distinguished Kiryu family
and now has the
powers of a vampire.
He'll become a
powerful asset to us.
-It's been a long
time, President.
-Uh?
-Goodness, how
you've grown, Zero.
Oh, my.
Is this your girlfriend?
-Huh?
-We've come to have a look
at the society's reports
from 10 years ago.
-10 years ago?
-Yes, I would like
to see them, as well.
-Hmm.
These records aren't meant
to be shown to the public.
I'm allowing you to see them
only because Cross asked me.
-Hey, Zero, a society president
is a pretty important person,
right?
So then I don't get it.
Why is he friends
with the headmaster?
-Do you mean to tell me that
you actually don't know?
PRESIDENT: We're here.
These are our archives.
The room holds extensive
records of the long war
between vampires
and vampire hunters.
ZERO: You want to stop?
-Uh?
I'm fine.
It's important
for me to be here.
I want to remember my past.
I'm just a little nervous.
Uh?
-Come with me, Zero.
Let us look at the
unsorted records.
CROSS: The records from 10
years ago seem to be here.
All right.
I gathered the records
dating from around the time
you were born.
You might notice something
if you study them yourself.
PRESIDENT: The
reports in here are
quite damaged and hard to read.
[door slams]
The papers were sent from places
where vampire hunters perished.
As you can see,
each one of these
has soaked up the
blood of our comrades.
[heartbeat]
[struggling to breathe]
YAGARI: Why?
Zero is a victim
of this association
no matter how you look at it,
and you send him to a soiree
and serve him up to a
room full of vampires?
-I don't see what
the problem is.
After all, nothing happened.
-But something
easily could have!
Or maybe that's exactly
what you were hoping for.
YUKI: "My last field report.
Three bodies
exterminated, as ordered.
Report complete.
Postscript: Starting tomorrow,
I will focus primarily
on my day job.
Kaien Cross."
Kaien Cross?
-Aaaah!
That's a report
from 16 years ago!
-You used to be a--
a vampire hunter?
-I'm sorry for not
telling you before.
You're my daughter.
I just didn't want you to know
that I used to kill vampires.
-Well, even so, you
are still my father.
What you used to
do doesn't matter.
-(TEARFULLY) Yuki!
YUKI: Besides, I
wouldn't have found it
if you hadn't gotten your
reports all mixed up.
What I want are the
reports from 10 years ago.
[breathing jaggedly]
-You seem to be
in a lot of agony.
Have you finally begun
to lapse into Level E?
-No, it's-- it's
the smell of blood.
-Poor boy.
You know what?
I'm going to help you
out with a little secret.
If you acquire the
blood of a Pureblood,
it may delay your falling
to Level E. You'll probably
feel better if you receive
some of Kaname Kuran's
blood-- assuming, of course,
that he will just give it
to you.
You know, if he's not
willing to give you any,
perhaps you should just take it.
Your situation may
seem impossible now,
but there are ways for
you to become stronger.
I mean, after all, you are the
other half of the Cursed Twins.
-What are you talking about?
YUKI: [cries out]
[door bursts open]
-Yuki, what's wrong?
What is that?
YUKI: I don't understand.
When I tried to
read it, the page
suddenly-- it's the
page that recounts
that winter, 10 years ago.
Why?
It's as though
something is trying
to prevent me from
remembering my past.
My memories start
with that night.
But before that--
-I'm scared.
[gasp]
-What?
-You're one of the Cursed Twins?
Who told you that?
-The association president.
And Ichiru, the other night.
-It's a myth unique to
vampire hunter families.
Twins are looked
upon as a curse.
But I have no idea why.
Hey, how is Yuki doing?
-She seems to have
suffered quite a shock.
-I see.
I guess that's to be expected.
-Vampire hunter families--
they don't have twins.
Even if there are
twins in the womb,
one will prove to be stronger
and devour the other,
and that's why only
one is ever born.
-A curse bestowed by vampires.
-But both Zero and
Ichiru were born,
and that may foreshadow a
curse of epic proportions.
-What are you getting at?
-Forget it.
Spoke with the top brass
at the association.
Seems they're up to something.
But as of right now, I
don't know what that is.
[knock]
-[gasp]
Who is it?
ZERO: It's me.
Can I come in?
-Mm.
-What's wrong?
-Uh, nothing.
I just got a little
sad when I suddenly
realized how empty the campus
is while everyone's on break.
[door closes]
-That's not the truth, is it?
What you were really doing
was thinking about your past,
about the page that burned at
the association headquarters.
-Mm.
It just feels like there's
something going on.
Someone's trying to
prevent me from remembering
my childhood and what
happened 10 years ago.
I'm not sure.
Maybe someone
erased my memories.
[gasp]
-Kaname!
That can't be.
But there's something I need
to find out from Kaname.
Hey, come on.
Why do you look so worried?
-You don't want to
worry about you, Yuki?
YUKI: That's not what I meant.
I don't want you to
waste what's left
of your time worrying about me.
Listen, don't worry.
I'm all right.
So please, just focus
on yourself now.
Zero.
-Yuki.
-What-- what?
-Zer-- [gasp]
ZERO: [gulping]
-Zero.
-Why don't you stop me?
Drinking your blood
like this, it's
the only way that I can survive!
Don't you understand?
You're my victim, Yuki!
-Zero.
-So that's why in return,
you have every single right
to make me suffer.
You can make me
worry, or drag me
into danger, whatever you want!
Drinking your blood like
this, It's the only way
I can survive, and
that's why I don't
mind using whatever's left of
my life if it's for you, Yuki.
[crying softly]
-I'm so scared.
Just what went on in my past?
[weeping]
KANAME: My apologies for
making you drop us off.
-It's no problem.
I was being picked up anyway.
But I am nervous, being
something to my grandfather's.
Regardless, are you
all right, Kaname?
Has something happened?
I'll be back as soon
as this errand is over.
KANAME: Very well.
YUKI: Welcome back, Kaname.
You see, the
headmaster just told me
that you were going
to come back early.
-I just wanted to see you, Yuki.
Here, I have a present.
-Huh?
Oh, thank you so much.
-It's a rose encased in resin.
These roses bloom only
once every 10 years.
It's a rare item, so
I decided to get it.
Would you have preferred food?
-Hm?
Uh, no!
I was just thinking
how beautiful it is.
-I have a life-sized
voodoo doll for you, Zero.
-I don't want it.
-Mm.
Kaname, wait.
I'd like to talk with
you later, if I could.
-Just the two of us?
-Y-yes.
-Fine then.
I'll see you tonight.
-Don't worry.
I'm fine.
I feel better after
crying all night.
HANABUSA: Lord Kaname, it seems
you decided to come back early.
-Yes.
I have urgent business.
Thank you for
lending us the villa.
-Please, don't mention it.
-What were you
searching for in here?
-Uh?
KANAME: Hanabusa?
-I just want to know what it is
you're planning, Lord Kaname.
-It would be wise not
to delve any further.
-(ANGRILY) Why
won't you tell me?
-Tell you what?
-Why is it that
your parents, Lord
and Lady Kuran, both of
them committed suicide?
I wanted to know
if it had something
to do with what you're planning.
-It wasn't suicide.
They were murdered.
-Your Pureblood
parents were murdered?
Who would do that?
-That's all that I
can say for right now.
I don't want you
to die for nothing.
-I don't care!
I want to be able to help you!
-I just told you.
It's better that you don't know.
-I'm sorry.
But please remember
that-- that I am always
on your side, so
never hesitate to ask.
KANAME: Hanabusa.
-Uh?
-I thought you
might suspect that I
was the one who
killed my parents.
-Huh?
-And the fact that you
didn't makes me happy.
-Mm.
ASATO ICHIJO: You came
without making a fuss.
TAKUMA: I don't want you
barging into the Academy again,
Grandfather.
-As a member of the
Senate, you know
the duties of the Ichijo family.
You know your role,
and that you're
educated to fulfill my wishes.
-Grandfather, I don't--
-There is someone who I
would like you to meet.
It's why I had you return.
-Uh?
[thud]
-Sorry to have kept you waiting.
How are you doing
this evening, my lord?
-Mm.
Not bad.
[gasp]
[MUSIC - KANON WAKESHIMA, "SUNA
NO OSHIRO"]
[music playing]