It looks like those
guys are bothering her.
You think we should call
Judgment and get them down here?
Here we go.
Never a dull moment
in this place.
Lovely Academy City.
Welcome to our
amazing city,
a thriving urban area
with a population of
twenty-three million.
Eighty percent of
which are students.
The city itself is like
a giant experiment,
standing at the very forefront
of the scientific community.
It's estimated that the
technology we use here,
is twenty to thirty
years more advanced
than you'll find anywhere
else in the world today.
Now, then.
Can you tell me what all the
students are here to study?
Esper powers!
I can't wait til I
find out my power!
The city has a tip--top
public safety system,
so you parents will
never have to worry
about your precious children
while they're here.
Please rest assured that...
Ow.
What was that?
Did we hit something?
The traffic signals are out.
Damn!
Nothing's going right.
Who in the world is that?
Hold it right there, punk!
In the name of Judgment!
I was right.
You're the hoodlum
they named in the alert,
aren't you?
It looks like today
isn't your day.
Damn.
This is Kuroko Shirai.
I've just captured
one of the criminals.
Uiharu, where are the remaining
targets to apprehend?
Take a left at the
end of the alley,
then another left five
meters after that.
Copy that! On it!
Halt, in the
name of Judgment!
We've been alerted
to your activities.
Come quietly, or I'll
be forced to....
What happened here?
Oh. Hey, Kuroko.
Sissy!
[Music]
Honestly!
How many times do I have to
say it before you understand?
Maintaining the public
safety of Academy City
is a job for Judgment,
not regular citizens.
You can't keep doing that
sort of thing on your own.
Are you listening to me?
Well, Sissy?
I can't help it if I
get there first, can I?
I'm always done by the
time you guys even show up.
You can't just beat
up another student
without authorization.
The city directors get all
twitchy when that happens.
In that case, maybe
you guys should try
getting there a little sooner.
Academy City isn't
living up to its name.
They've got security
posted all over,
but they can't even
eliminate petty criminals.
They can claim to be
scientifically advanced
all they want, but...
Sissy...
Chaser!
I don't see how those advances
really impact our lives.
What am I going
to do with you?
How come you still insist
on wearing those dowdy
shorts under your skirt?
Why were you even looking?
I wear these because
it's easier to...
Trouble detected
with vending machine
seven--one--one--six--five.
Destruction of
property suspected.
Now, was that
really necessary?
You could've gotten
into trouble.
Oh, no.
We're going to
have to hurry.
Hm? Oh. That's right.
We have our System
Scan today, huh?
Those are waves.
A star.
Waves.
Circle.
Next, 38 degrees.
Right.
Off by point two millimeters.
Very good.
Next student please.
Recording 78 meters
and 23 centimeters.
Distance from target,
54 centimeters.
Overall rating, Level 4.
I'm feeling a little bit
off today for some reason.
Maybe my work with Judgment
yesterday exhausted my...
Making excuses for
your poor performance?
Don't you think that's
a little pathetic?
Even for you, Shirai.
Shut it, Mitsuko Kongo.
At the rate you're going,
it's pretty obvious I'll
reach Level 5 before you do.
-Won't that be exciting?
-Hmph.
I'd greatly appreciate it
if you'd avoid comparing your
abilities with my powers.
The differences between grasping
three--dimensional space
and eleven--dimensional
space are simply...
It will be a nice change.
I've always found it annoying
to have a first--year
student like you
talking down to
someone like me.
She never developed
the ability to listen
to anybody's voice
but her own.
Geez. Was that some
kind of explosion?
Since you transferred in
this term as a second year,
there are probably some gaps in
your knowledge of the school.
A certain student is
having her abilities
tested at the
pool right now.
And she's the real
Ace of Tokiwadai.
If they didn't use the water
in the pool to act as a buffer,
they couldn't accurately
measure her destructive powers.
What do you think?
Are you ready to face one of
those blasts head--on, huh?
Recording initial shot speed
at one--thousand--thirty
meters per second.
Rapid--fire ability,
eight shots per minute.
Pattern grouping,
eighteen point nine millimeters.
Overall rating, Level 5.
Huh? You heard it from
across the school grounds?
It was incredibly loud.
Girls were nearly jumping
out of their skins.
Good grief.
It's so annoying that's the only
way to get an accurate reading.
Sometimes I think an
ability like yours
would be a lot more
convenient than mine.
Isn't it amazing how the
grass is always greener
on the other side?
Yeah, yeah, spout all the
platitudes you want to...
Say whatever you want.
It doesn't change the fact
that you're Tokiwadai's Ace.
You can thrust out
your chest with pride
based upon that alone.
The Ace, am I?
Although, I may be wrong.
This small chest of yours
might be too modest
and bashful to be thrust out.
But, oh! It's this very modesty
that lays at the heart of your
undeniable sensuality, Sissy!
This simple yet
elegant temptation
is almost too much
for one girl to bear!
My poor heart might break!
There's already something
broken in your head.
I was just trying to
bond with you, Sissy.
Shut up!
-Let's see.
-U--i--ha--ru!
Oh, I see that
you're sporting
the light pink
polka--dots today.
I can't believe you!
What do you think
you're doing, Saten?
Oh, come on, just relax.
We're classmates,
aren't we?
There's no need to be
so bashful about it.
Here, let's try again.
It'll make you feel better.
You're awful, you know that?
Sorry, sorry.
I got carried away.
Want to see mine
to even the score?
No, thank you.
Sometimes I think
you're pure evil.
Oh, I forgot.
How'd it go?
How did what go?
Well, what do
you think, silly?
You had your System Scan.
Oh.
An absolute disaster.
I'm still ranked a Level 1,
just like I've always been
way back to grade school.
You should have heard
my homeroom teacher,
"Are those flowers on your
head just for show?
Use their blooming power
to encourage your own
abilities to blossom!"
Oh, wow.
There's so much
in that speech
I could make fun of,
it's too easy.
But, that aside,
try to keep your chin up, 'kay?
Level 1 is a whole lot better
than nothing, if you ask me.
Unlike my pathetic
Level Zero.
I am officially
incompetent.
Now, now.
Don't worry about me.
I make sure to enjoy every
day as much as I can.
Long as I do that,
it's okay!
That's a good philosophy.
Here. Listen to this.
It'll cheer you up.
It's Hitotsui Hajime!
-What's this song?
-You wouldn't have heard it.
I downloaded the
pre--release early.
The album this song is on
actually goes on sale today.
Do you still buy the CD even
after you've downloaded it?
Of course I do.
But I still like
entering to win stuff
like this limited--release
download.
Because that is the
mark of a true fan!
Now, come with me so
we can buy that CD!
I can't go with you.
I have a meeting with
Kuroko Shirai today.
That name sounds familiar.
Is she that girl who's
in Judgment with you?
My fondest wish is
about to come true.
Today I'm going to
meet Mikoto Misaka.
She's one of only seven Level
5's in all of Academy City!
The Ace of Tokiwadai!
I think she's amazing!
Really, a Level 5 from
Tokiwadai Middle School?
I bet she's just
another arrogant jerk
who flaunts her power
while looking down her
nose at the rest of us.
No, she's not!
People like her
are all the same.
They treat anyone on the
lower Levels with contempt.
I think they're disgusting.
And she'll be worse since
she's the darling of Tokiwadai.
The darling of Tokiwadai.
I love that!
I get to meet somebody
who's no simple student,
but a darling!
Know what I think?
You're so starry--eyed
over meeting a celebrity
that it's addled
your brains.
I'm excited about
meeting her
because I'm sure she's
a very nice person.
And the anticipation hasn't
affected my brain at all!
Hey, I know! Why don't
you come along, Saten?
I don't really
know about that.
Oh, come on.
It'll be so much fun!
Yeah, maybe, but I just
don't think tha...
You don't get a chance
like this very often!
Hey, I said I wasn't sure!
Let me think a second.
Uiharu!
One of my fans?
She's a girl I
know from Judgment.
She takes care of my backup
at the 177th Branch.
She's a big supporter.
She's always asking
to meet you,
even if it's only
for a few minutes.
Now Sissy, I know
that lately your fans
have been becoming more
and more annoying
and you have little enough
patience for meeting them.
But I think you'll find
that Uiharu is different.
She's a reasonable,
polite girl.
Besides which,
she's one of the few people
I actually consider
my friend.
So, really I'm asking
you to do it for me.
And since I know
how busy you are,
I've taken the
liberty of arranging
an orderly schedule
for the day.
I'm pretty sure you'll
find it to your liking.
Hey!
Let's see,
what have we here?
"Date plan with Sissy
using Uiharu as a ruse.
Part one, foster friendship
at a family restaurant.
Part two, lingerie shopping.
Purchase 'big
moment' underwear.
Part three, shopping
at a perfume store.
Purchase aphrodisiac.
Ditch Uiharu and
go to an upscale
but discreet
hotel with Sissy."
In other words, you're
just using this reasonable,
polite girl you
call your friend
in order to fulfill your
own perverted desires.
Is that right?
Not really.
I thought you were trying to
make my life less stressful!
You've got it all wrong,
Sissy I swear.
It wasn't like that.
Owowowowowow!
Even so...
You say she's a friend
of yours, Kuroko,
so what choice is there?
Oh, my!
Sissy! Sweet Sissy!
Kuroko...
At last you reveal how deeply
you care about my happiness!
I could die!
I could die right now
from hearing that!
Excuse me, miss ...
Ah, Sissy, my heart is about to
burst! I can't contain myself!
I'm terribly sorry,
but you're beginning to
frighten the other customers.
Now that that's
out of the way,
it's time to get to
the introductions.
This is Kazari Uiharu
from Judgment.
She's a first--year at
Sakugawa Middle School.
Oh! Pleased to meet you!
I mean, it's really an honor.
And this is?
Hi there. My name's Ruiko Saten,
a classmate of Uiharu's.
She decided to drag
me along with her,
so here I am.
And by the way my power
rating is Level Zero.
So there!
Saten, why would
you say that?
Well, hello, Uiharu.
Saten.
I'm another friend
of Kuroko's.
Misaka.
Oh, it's a pleasure
to meet you.
Yes, yes, such a pleasure.
Okay, the introductions
have been completed
without incident.
The timetable has been
thrown off somewhat,
but I've made this
schedule for today
that I think should
work for every...
Okay.
Well, standing around here
isn't very much fun, is it?
I have an idea.
Let's go to the arcade.
Go to the arcade?
What do you think?
Come on, Kuroko.
Let's go.
I think it's
beneath you, Sissy.
I guess playing
games in the arcade
and browsing magazines
is fun enough,
but shouldn't you have some
more dignified hobbies?
You could try arranging
flowers, maybe,
-or playing the harp.
-Here you go.
Please. Why should
I waste my time
stuffing flowers in a vase
or learning an instrument
no one knows how to play?
Please, take one.
Have a good afternoon!
You know something.
She doesn't act like
some arrogant celebrity.
Yeah and she doesn't look down
her nose at us at all, either.
What's on the flyer?
It looks like there's a
new crepe stand opening,
and the first one
hundred customers
get a Gekota figurine
as a free gift.
Now that's one cheesy
looking character.
I mean, who would go for
something like that these days?
Oh, sorry.
Is there something wrong?
What's the hold up, Sissy?
Something the matter?
Oh, I see.
You're interested in the
new crepe stand, aren't you?
Or something else?
Is it the free giveaway
they're offering
that caught your eye?
No! I don't know what
you're talking about.
Why would I care about
this Gekota guy?
I mean, he's just a frog,
a stupid amphibian.
What kind of girl
would be interested in
some dumb thing like that?
Wow.
There are so many people.
What's with all the
kids running around?
Remember our break will
only be one hour long.
Everybody please
stay close.
You don't want
to miss the bus.
It's some kind of tour.
We must have bad timing.
I'll go see if I can find
a free bench to save for us.
Oh, then, why don't
I go with you?
Saten, we're finding
a place to sit.
Will you get
something for us?
Don't worry, we'll pay
you back for it later.
-Thanks a lot!
-Huh? Wait-
Huh? What's wrong?
Nothing.
Would you like to
switch places with me?
No, it doesn't matter
to me who goes first.
We're just here for crepes,
so as long as I get one,
I'm fine.
All right!
I got a Gekota!
-So did I!
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your free gift.
You're lucky.
It's the last one we have.
Great, thank you.
Oh, hold on.
The last, you said?
Um, Misaka ...
It's all yours
if you'd like it.
Are you sure?
You really mean it?
Yeah, no problem.
Thank you so much!
Y... you're welcome.
Come on, Sissy,
just try one bite.
-You know you want to!
-I said I don't want any!
Who chooses anchovies
as a topping, anyway?
Open wide and
say, "Aaahhhh."
No, just leave
me alone already!
She's nice, isn't she?
Misaka, I mean.
Not at all what you'd expect
for somebody so well known.
She's not stuck up at all.
Just approachable
and friendly.
You sure about that?
Here.
-Uh, what?
-Would you like to taste it?
Go on try some as a
thank you for before.
Absolutely not!
I won't stand
for this, Sissy!
I'm right here, yet you
offer somebody else
what is rightfully mine?
I'm not sure I can keep
up with your friends.
They're so energetic.
Huh?
It's nothing.
I was just noticing
that bank over there.
Why would the security
shutters be down
in the middle of the day?
What was that crash?
Uiharu, I want you
to contact Antiskill
and request some officers to
our location right away.
Yeah, I'm on it!
Wait up, Kuroko!
No you don't.
Stay right where you are.
Like I've told you a
million times,
public safety is the concern
of those of us in Judgment.
Please do me a favor and just
behave yourself this time.
Yes, that's correct.
There's a bank
robbery in progress
across from the public square
on the edge of District 7.
Requesting Antiskill.
Come on, you idiots.
-We've gotta move it, or...
-Stop right there!
I am a Judgment officer,
and I am placing
you under arrest
for destruction of
property and bank robbery.
Who does this
kid think she is?
Judgment must be
short--staffed.
Hey, little lady.
You should find
somewhere else to play,
or you could end
up getting hurt.
Is that the most intimidating
line you can come up with?
You're not much of a
professional, are you?
-Wha-?
-Damn brat!
She's amazing!
That's Kuroko for you.
Please, stay here.
It's not safe to leave
the square right now.
-Let go!
-What's wrong here?
Misaka!
We're missing one of the
boys who was on the tour!
He said he left
something on the bus,
and then he went
to look for it.
All right. Uiharu and I
will see what we can...
I want to help, too!
All right, then.
Let's split up
and look for him.
It's too late to back
down, now, girlie.
A pyrokineticist?
All right.
-Hey, watch it!
-Don't run away from me!
Run away?
-She's gone!
-Who says I'm running?
What? She's a teleporter?
You should probably
stop resisting me.
Or I'll take
drastic measures.
Like teleporting this directly
into your body, for example.
Find anything?
No, nothing!
Where in the world has
that kid disappeared to?
What do we have here?
Perfect! You're
coming with me.
What are you
doing, mister?
-Who are you?
-Never mind, just move it.
Hurry up!
I have to stop him.
Maybe we should have another
look around the square.
Hey! What do you want?
Go away!
Let go!
Damn it!
He hurt Saten!
Kuroko!
From here on out, this fight
is a personal one for me.
I hate to do this,
but it's too late.
I'm going to have
to get involved now.
Crap, I just remembered.
They say there's this
scary girl in Judgment.
She's a teleporter who will
beat you up inside and out
until you wish that
you'd never been born.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Damn her!
I'm not gonna
turn tail and run.
What's even worse,
apparently this teleporter has
given herself, heart and soul,
to a powerful electromaster.
Go ahead.
I'm happy to take
you out, too.
That's right.
That girl over there is
one of the most powerful
of the twenty--three
million people in the city.
Out of the seven Level 5's,
she's ranked third.
Railgun.
Mikoto Misaka.
My Sissy.
The pride and joy of
Tokiwadai Middle School.
The ultimate, unstoppable
shock princess!
Wow.
That was incredible.
There were zero injuries
among the general population.
Please, keep walking forward
in an orderly fashion.
Your pyrotechnic abilities
weren't all that bad, you know.
Unless I miss my guess,
you'd be right around a Level 3.
You probably got caught up in
the excitement of your powers
and went down
the wrong path.
Take a good look at yourself
and the consequences
of your actions,
and maybe you can
make a fresh start.
You were great!
Thank you so much!
No, really.
It's nothing.
I don't how I can
ever repay you.
Thank the nice lady.
Thank you for helping
me, nice lady!
You handled that situation
pretty well, Saten.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I think it was downright
heroic of you.
-You, too, Misaka.
-There you are, Sissyyyyyyy!
Kuroko, let go of me!
-You're making a scene!
-There you are, Saten!
Look at your face!
Are you hurt badly?
Oh, no. I'm okay, really.
It looks bad.
Are you sure?
Misaka's so brave.
She was the real hero today.
That's it.
I've had enough!
[Music]
My idol Misaka was great today.
She sure was.
Saten, stop it.
What are you pouring
water on my head for?
We don't want your
flowers to wither.
You need to be
ready for next time!