From what we've learned today,
it should be apparent
that this aspect of
Academy City's
ability--developing curriculum
is the most important.
Personal Reality.
To put it another way,
it is the acquiring of
a reality unto oneself.
This is the basis for the
development of Esper powers.
Once you understand
Personal Reality,
you must begin to explore
quantum theory as well.
This concept is based on
the uncertainty principle
postulated by the German
physicist Heisenberg.
Now, Personal Reality
and quantum theory
are connected because they
have something in common.
Both concepts are
rooted in probability.
For example, let's look
at Schrodinger's cat.
Huh? A cold?
Yeah. I only have
a slight fever,
but it won't seem to budge.
Okay.
Try to get some rest
and feel better.
Saten!
Ruiko Saten!
Uh, yes?
You look like you
already know the material.
Maybe you'd like to explain
that last point to the class.
Oh, sure!
Let's see.
One sec.
Never mind.
I suggest you study up on
Personal Reality for next time.
That's all for today.
Who cares about theories
and thought experiments?
I wish they'd teach us
how to level up faster.
That would be useful.
It's really hot
out today, isn't it?
What's with the face?
You look super grouchy.
I can't believe that
Hatsuya Kaitabi was a Level 2.
It just doesn't make
any sense to me.
Kaitabi?
Oh.
The guy behind the
graviton attacks.
But, all of the destruction,
he would have to be at least
a Level 4 to cause that.
Right. And that can
only mean one thing.
Well, it has to mean ...
I have no idea.
What does it mean?
Hey, don't look at me.
That's kinda what
I was asking you.
You're stressing.
Let's take a break.
It might help
you to cool off.
What do you want?
Just whatever you're
having, Sissy.
You know what I've
always found strange?
How whenever you
hear a wind chime,
it makes you feel a
little bit cooler.
Yeah. It does that
because of synesthesia.
What's synesthesia?
Thank you for waiting.
Here you go.
Two strawberries.
It's the reception
of multiple sensations
from a single stimulus.
And we're paying
separately, by the way.
You were the one
who suggested it.
I thought it
was your treat.
Huh? What's that?
Oh, nothing at all.
So, anyway, seeing
reddish colors
makes you feel
warmer, right?
And in the same way,
seeing bluish tones
makes you feel cooler.
Reds are warm colors, whereas
blues are cool colors.
Right. And this shaved
ice is strawberry--red.
I get it.
The fact that it's
such a bright red
intensifies the fruitiness
of the sensation.
Did your brain freeze?
Aw.
Misaka Shirai!
Hey you guys!
Hey, Saten.
Those ices look delicious.
Yeah, we feel your pain.
That happened to both
of us a second ago.
You know what's
going to happen,
but you can't
stop eating it.
Ooh. Did you guys
get strawberry?
Mm--hmm.
Here, would you
like to taste?
Aw, that's so nice of you.
Don't mind if I do!
Mmm, yummy!
Let me give you a bite
of lemon in return.
Cool, thank you.
What? What do you
think you're doing?
Uh, tasting each
other's flavors.
You're tasting her flavor.
Tasting.
Flavor.
I could have done that!
Kuroko, you're a
complete idiot!
Oh, okay.
Then why don't
you kiss my ...
I mean taste
my flavor, too?
What would be the point?
You got the same
flavor I did.
Stupid! Stupid!
I am such a moron!
Hey, I just realized
Uiharu isn't with you today.
She stayed home
from school
because, apparently,
she's got a cold.
I was just on my way to drop
off some medicine for her.
-Is it really bad?
-No.
She doesn't think
it's anything serious,
but I know how
annoying colds can be.
You know, you guys
could come along, too.
Here we are!
We all wanted to
check up on you.
-Sorry if we're intruding.
-Hope it isn't a bad time.
Thanks guys.
That's sweet.
Don't worry about it.
Now, hold still.
It says 37 point three.
Well, that's
slightly high,
so you should
probably stay in bed
and be sure to cover up
so you don't catch a chill.
You know, Saten, it might
help prevent a chill
if you'd stop flipping
my skirt up all the time.
Don't give them
the wrong idea!
As Uiharu's best friend,
I just want to make sure she's
wearing panties every day
like she's supposed to.
It's my duty.
Of course I wear panties!
Every day!
Yes, of course.
We know you do.
Now lie down before
you get any worse.
I'll go fix up a
cool towel for you.
Oh, I wanted to
ask you, Shirai,
have there been any developments
in the graviton attacker case?
There is one
thing, I guess.
It isn't really
much help, though.
We know that the person who's
responsible for the attacks
has a Level 2 ranking.
But what he did was
unmistakably Level 4 stuff.
So the only development
so far is the discovery
that there's even more we
don't understand about it?
Yeah, that's
pretty much it.
Now that I think about it,
didn't you mention
something before
about a machine called
the Level Upper?
Huh?
It raises a person's
ability level?
Yeah, but like I said,
it's just a rumor
all totally unsubstantiated.
So there's no
proof it exists?
None at all.
The stories about
it are all mixed up.
It's nothing more than
an urban legend, really.
Oh, well.
I suppose there's no way
it could be that convenient,
is there?
The truth is, this isn't the
first time a person's Level
as shown in the
databank doesn't match
what they've
actually done.
We've seen situations
like this more than once
that girl with the funny
eyebrows and the stun gun
and the bank robber who
was a pyrokineticist.
I use those as examples
because they're ones you
already know about, Sissy.
But Judgment has recorded
even more instances
of an Esper's ability not
matching their attack.
Are you saying?
There really is such a thing
as a Level Upper somewhere?
Is there anything else
you can tell us about it?
Huh? Let me see.
There is something,
but it could be another rumor.
I heard somewhere about
people who use the Level Upper
posting to some kind of
message board on the net.
Do you know which
message board it is?
Um, let me think.
I don't know.
Let's see.
Take a look, Saten.
Could it be this one?
Ah, there it is!
Nicely done, Uiharu!
Now if we can only
determine their identities
and where they hang out.
I can't speak to
their identities,
but as for their
hangouts, look.
They seem to get together
at this restaurant
pretty frequently.
Thanks a lot, Uiharu.
I'm gonna look into it.
Oh, and get well soon!
Get back here!
This is a job for me!
Not you!
Sissy! Listen to me
when I'm talking to you!
Sissy!
Do you think they're
gonna be okay?
With those two, we don't
have anything to worry about.
I mean, Kuroko's a Level 4,
and Misaka is a Level 5.
What could they
need us for, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
Say, Uiharu,
what if we could get a
hold of the Level Upper?
Do you think we
could really use it
to increase our
ability levels?
Who knows?
But in any case,
cheating is wrong.
Yeah, I know.
Just hypothetically.
I would never actually
do it, of course.
Hey! I've got an idea!
The teacher called on
me at school today,
and I had no clue
how to answer.
Think you could
explain this to me?
I'm sick and you're asking me
to help you do your schoolwork?
I bet you're hungry.
I could make
something for you.
And now you're trying to bribe
me with the promise of food?
All right, then. Fine.
I won't ask again.
Well, I guess I could eat.
So, anyway.
He told me to study up
on Personal Reality,
but I just don't get
the concept, you know?
Yeah, it's complicated.
I feel like I've heard something
about it before, though.
You have to create a
reality unto yourself.
A reality unto oneself?
A reality unto you.
A reality unto me.
What are these
realities, anyway?
Delusions, maybe?
Oh. That might be it.
-Huh?
-Well, not delusions exactly.
Those are totally unreal.
But what about the assumptions
we make about the world.
The power of
our own belief?
The power of our
own belief, huh?
I'm only a Level 1, though.
I'm sure somebody else
could explain it better.
That was great.
I mean, when you first used the
phrase "reality unto oneself,"
I was confused.
But I feel like I'm
starting to understand.
Maybe I just have
to believe enough
and then my Level
will go up someday.
You'll be fine, Saten.
I know you.
You're too stubborn
to give up easily.
Sometimes you say
the rudest things.
You know that?
This is it.
Well, shall we go in?
Sissy, this doesn't
concern you.
Maybe but the people
we're looking for
might recognize you as
a member of Judgment.
-But, I...
-Look, it'll be fine.
Just let me handle it, okay?
You lay low at another
table and wait for me.
What's she planning to do?
I've got a bad feeling
about this idea.
-Okay, here I go!
-No, hold on!
Please don't go
in there, Sissy!
You came here looking
for information
on the Level Upper, huh?
I came across
your message board
and I thought it was
super interesting,
so I came here
to ask about it
because I know this is
where you guys hang out.
Please! I'm begging you!
So, will you tell me?
Don't know what
you're talkin' about.
Now scram already.
Come on, I'm not
asking very much.
You're buggin' us.
Shouldn't a squirt like
you be in bed by now?
This isn't working.
I knew from the beginning
it was going to fail.
Hey, now. I'm not
as young as I look!
You don't look like
such a little girl
from where I'm sitting.
As a matter of fact,
you're just my type.
Aw! You really mean it?
So about the Level Upper.
Don't get ahead of
yourself, sweetie.
That kinda information
doesn't come cheap, you know.
Oh. Well, I guess I have a
little money I can give you.
Yeah, money is
great and all,
but I actually had another
form of payment in mind,
if you get what I'm saying.
Hey now, don't get
the wrong impression.
I'm not that kind of girl.
I mean, I only just met
you tonight after all.
Are you sure
money won't do?
What was that earlier about
not being a little girl?
I'm... I'm in a really
rough spot right now.
What's going on with
all the sniffling?
I don't know what to do.
I don't have
anywhere else to turn
other than the Level Upper.
So, please.
Won't you help me?
Whatever,
just quit crying.
I'm just, I'm just so ...
That uniform.
Isn't it from Tokiwadai?
Yeah, now that
you mention it.
If we play it right
she could make for a
seriously good money tree.
Hey, uh ...
All right, kid.
Quit crying.
It's irritating me.
We'll give you
the information.
Really? Thanks so much!
We should step outside.
We're not gonna say
anything about it in here.
Let's go.
Okay, then.
This is far enough.
Nobody's going to
interfere with us out here.
Great!
Why don't you start by
giving us all the cash
you've got on you?
Oh, and you can hand
over your debit card
and PIN number, too.
And any credit
cards, of course.
Being a Tokiwadai lady,
I'm sure you've got a few.
Um, well, I did withdraw
some cash before I came here,
but I can't just
give it all to you.
Oh?
You wanna hear what
we have to say?
Then you'd better
hurry and pay up.
Do it now.
Give us every last
dime you've got
unless you want us
to strip search you
and get your
money that way.
How annoying.
Look, just hand over
the money or we'll...
Whoa! Are you okay?
You! You little brat!
I've had enough of this.
I was trying to go about this
in a more civilized manner,
but you guys had to
go and get nasty.
Now tell me everything you
know about the Level Upper.
I'd change my tone
if I were you,
though we're
happy to show you
just what our powered--up
strength can do.
More of them.
Have all these guys really
used this Level Upper thing?
With this many of them at
the same Level as Kaitabi...
Yeah, I'm gonna
give it to you now.
Take my Level 2...
There were a lot of
you guys to deal with.
I'm afraid things were
bound to get a little messy.
You really did a number
on them, didn't you?
It ... it's the boss!
Hey, what's going on?
What were you trying to do to
that little lady over there?
We're sorry, Boss.
Shamelessly trying to
steal a young girl's money?
But, Boss...
Are you talking back to me?
To me?
I... I'm sorry!
I'm not the one you
need to apologize to.
Go on, all of you!
Uh, my bad. Sorry.
That's not gonna cut it.
I sincerely apologize.
Us, too!
Well, that should
square things, right?
I hope you can
forgive them.
You guys!
Get out of here!
Ma'am! We're going!
All right. So you're their boss?
In that case, you must know all
about the Level Upper, too.
Let's set that aside.
You gave my underlings
a serious working over.
I hope you're prepared
to answer for that.
Prepared to ...
but, uh ...
you just made them
apologize to me.
Well, that was that,
and now this is this.
Honor demands that I pay
you back for what you did.
Let's go!
Whoa! What's happening?
The ground's shifting.
That would be my ability.
It's called Flux Coat.
With it, I have the power
to control the viscosity
of the asphalt.
Whatcha gonna do?
There's nowhere to run.
Nice try, girl, but that
attack won't-What the?
She vanished!
That wasn't bad.
Impossible! How are
you staying up there?
An electrical current.
It creates a
magnetic field.
All I have to do is direct it
toward the rebar in the wall.
I'll show you!
Well?
Do you feel like telling
me what you know yet,
or shall we continue?
I see now.
You didn't put all the
power of your ability
into your first
attack, did you?
And just now you
intentionally missed me
with that blast as well.
Exactly.
Now, be a good girl
and tell me...
Screw you! I'm not
declaring defeat yet!
If you call yourself an Esper,
give me your best!
You want to try your
will against mine?
You think a little electric
shock can beat me?
Then go ahead and try.
We'll see who wins!
That sounds like a challenge.
Well, I'm happy to
take you up on it.
Sissy, hold on!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
No, I really don't
think you do!
Stop, Sissy!
Come on, Uiharu, admit it.
You want to become a
higher level Esper, too.
You know, like
Misaka and Shirai.
Well, having a high ability
level would be pretty awesome,
and it would offer a
lot of opportunities
for academic advancement.
It's why we're here.
If we wanted a normal
school experience,
we could get that
anywhere else.
People flock to this city
because they're fascinated
by Esper powers.
That's the reason it exists.
Before I came here
I wondered what my ability
would turn out to be;
what kind of secret power
I could have hidden in me.
I couldn't sleep the
night before I left
I was so excited
about it all.
And then I had my first
System Scan, and they told me,
"You have absolutely
no discernable talent.
You are a Level
Zero, Saten."
That was hard to hear.
Really hard.
It made me sad.
I know how you feel.
I really do.
I don't have much of an ability
level myself, you know.
I'm a One.
But look at the
friends I've made.
I get to work side
by side with Shirai.
And you and I have
fun all the time.
I mean, if I hadn't
have come here,
I never would have gotten the
chance to meet all of you guys.
So, as far as
I'm concerned,
coming here was a worthwhile
experience if only for that.
Uiharu.
You're adorable!
Sometimes you say the sweetest
things, you know that?
And to say thank you, I'll
sponge bathe your entire body!
That's okay!
I can reach.
I don't need help!
A blackout?
This is why I was trying
to tell you not to do it.
It's not my fault, is it?
How was I supposed to know
that there was something
like this around here?
Like I said,
I knew there was.
You can't just show up at
the last second like that!
And what am I gonna
do about my shoes?
I'd say that's
your problem.
I guess I lost after all.
So much for that plan.
All that and I didn't end
up with any information.
Kuroko!
Come on. We've got a
new problem on our hands.
Hatsuya Kaitabi
is unconscious?
I don't know
all the details.
He suddenly passed out while
Antiskill was questioning him.
Kuroko Shirai, with Judgment.
How is he?
We're doing
everything we can,
but he shows no signs of
regaining consciousness.
Um, well, I don't know
if this could have
something to do with it,
but I punched him
pretty hard in the face.
No. He doesn't exhibit any
significant head trauma.
For that matter, we can't find
anything wrong with him at all.
We looked him
over thoroughly.
He simply lost
consciousness.
So you don't know
what caused it
or how long it will go on.
There is one unusual thing.
This week we've had multiple
patients brought in here
with the same symptoms.
I hate to have
to admit it,
but this is beyond
the capabilities
of this hospital
and its staff.
So, I've called in an
outside specialist
in cerebrophysiology.
Sorry to have
kept you waiting.
I came here at the request
of the Mizuho Systems
Hospital Director.
My name is Harumi Kiyama.
Thank you for coming.
Why are you here?
I can't find anything
concrete on the Level Upper.
Maybe it really is nothing
more than just a rumor.
Guess I'll download
some new songs on here.
Is that a hidden link?
Could this be?
The Level Upper
actually exists?
Do people who use it
ever go back to normal?
Huh? I was talking to you.
Where did you go?
Saten?