It's been a long time Mii.
Kurozuma.
You're really alive.
It looks that way.
But why?
Why didn't you contact me.
All this time, not
a word from you...!
I thought... you were dead.
Don't worry about me.
I can easily
disappear again.
Come back!
Please don't go.
[Music]
So Konori and Kurozuma
know each other?
Mm--hmm.
She hasn't
explained exactly
how they're
acquainted, though.
But I thought Kurozuma
was part of that gang.
He's supposedly the
boss of Big Spider.
According to
our information.
It makes no sense.
How would she know
someone like that?
She wouldn't be
friends with a guy
who goes around
attacking girls!
Oh... um...
that's not him...
This is a different
Kurozuma...
How do I explain it...?
It's like, uh...
You wanna chime in...?
I could use some help
clarifying this thing.
People connect in
mysterious ways sometimes.
When it comes to
situations like this,
I find it best to remain
a silent observer.
Oh, man, this
is bugging me!
Why does it have to
be so confusing?!
Maybe I'll just go
straight to Konori
and ask her about it myself.
Good luck.
Nobody's seen her
for a few days now.
She hasn't shown
up at the branch.
-Not at all?
-Nope...
and I can't get through to
her on her cell, either...
It's weird for
her to disappear
when we're in the middle
of a big case like this.
Fretting about her vanishing
act won't do us any good...
We're not going to
find any answers
by sitting here all day.
It's time for us to take
this show on the road.
What are you
talking about?
The road to where?
Coming!
Hello. Who are you?
Oh, um...
We were looking
for Mii Konori,
but maybe we got the
wrong place... Sorry.
Oh, you're junior
Judgment officers...
Sorry. I'm afraid
you're out of luck.
Mii isn't here right now.
Oh... she isn't?
I wanted to hear more about
this Kurozuma character.
Yeah... that's a real shame.
All right, then.
We'll try again later...
Sorry to bother you.
Wait... don't go.
What am I gonna
do with her?
Making all of you
worry along with me.
It's okay. Thanks.
So then...
Kurozuma has
returned, has he?
He's still alive
after all this time.
Then you know
who Kurozuma is?
Can you tell us how he and
Konori know each other?
Just slow down a second...
Maybe you could tell me
more about yourselves first.
I see.
Then it's no wonder.
So... anyway...
It would be great
if you'd tell us about
Konori's past involvement
with Kurozuma...
We don't know
anything really,
but I thought maybe she
apprehended him sometime before?
No, you're wrong
about that...
Very wrong...
You see, Mii was actually
part of Big Spider once.
No way...! Impossible!
I don't believe it.
Neither do I. She's a
senior member of Judgment!
You must be mistaken!
That's who she is now...
But she used to have a
little bit of a wild streak.
She had a wild streak??
I hate to speak out of
turn about somebody's past,
but it makes
no sense to me.
Wild child or not,
the fact remains that Konori
is a Level Three esper...
She could've become involved in
any number of organizations.
With so many
options open
why in the world would
she choose to run
with a group of non--espers
like Skill--Out?
It's not as
simple as that...
Have you ever hit a wall
when it came to your ability?
She had a difficult time
trying to get past hers,
and the depression became
too much to handle.
Back then things
were hard for her.
She felt like no
matter where she went,
she didn't belong.
One day that changed.
She found a
group of people
who made her
feel less alone.
Skill--Out was
a gang, true...
but they did nothing more
harmful than hang out together
and goof around
a little bit.
Honestly...
I was worried
at first, too.
She was intentionally
hiding the fact
that she was an
esper from them...
It didn't seem
right somehow.
But...
"Big Spider is the
first place I've found
where I've felt
free to be myself."
So she said...
and I believed her.
Being yourself.
Alienation...
self--discovery...
Everyone who lives
in Academy City
is sure to experience
those at some point.
It's a fact of life here,
like chicken pox.
The problem with that is you
only catch chicken pox once.
What's wrong, Sissy?
-Yo.
-Oh. Hey...
I was just...
So, Mii... word on the street
is you're a Level Two.
If that's true,
you shouldn't be here.
Let me stay!
I don't have anywhere
else to go...
Please don't make me!
I guess espers have
problems of their own, huh?
Well... okay then.
However...
What're you going
to do next year...?
And the year after that?
Just something you might
want to be thinking about.
What now?
I don't get it.
What don't you get?
It's bad enough already
that Konori used to be
a member of Skill-- Out.
But now she's missing all
of this Judgment work, too.
The two things
seem related.
I'm sure Konori is-
She's past all that...
Whatever happened before,
Konori's a hard--working
member of Judgment now.
She's strict sometimes,
that's true...
but she's still
nice to us...
and she's dependable.
That's the Konori we know.
So why is she behaving
like this now?
I have a feeling it's
not as cut and dried
as you make it sound, Misaka.
Just like everybody,
who Konori is,
is a result of who she was.
Besides, it sounds like
that part of her past
has special meaning to her...
and is hard to let go.
No...! It's not
like that, I swear!
I'm not trying to side
against you, Misaka!
Anyway.
I just don't get it.
What gives...?
Where is everybody?
What do you expect
after what happened?
Not many guys wanted
to hang around.
Yeah, I guess so.
Hey... does this mean the
Kurozuma we know is an imposter?
There's no way he is...!
Kurozuma is still
the same guy we knew!
Yeah... but if that's true,
why'd he look
so spooked
when the guy called
him Hebitani?
You saw that too, huh?
Hard to miss...
He almost looked scared.
What was that?
Who almost looked scared?
Oh... hey, Kurozuma.
You've got time
on your hands
to stand around
here doubting me?
Then you have time
to get out there,
find that poser,
and kill 'im!
There isn't enough
room in Academy City
for two Wataru Kurozumas.
Just me!
-R... Right!
-Okay, let's move!
-Let's go!
-Come on, hurry it up!
Faster, idiots!
Yeah, hello?
Who else would it be?
Huh?... The Capacity
Down system...?
Yeah... we're using the
hell out of it, all right.
Oh, shut up...!
Things are a big
mess here, too.
We don't have time
for esper hunting now!
What did you just say?
She looks sad.
Has Misaka been
like that for long?
Oh yeah... all day.
Hey, guys...
I've got an email
from Antiskill.
Let's see here...
"To counteract the esper
hunts by Skill--Out,
Antiskill headquarters
will be mobilizing tomorrow.
At ten a.m.,
units will move into
School District Ten, Area G,
commonly known as Strange.
It will be a
comprehensive sweep."
Mii... you forgot something.
I knew this is
where you would be.
Misaka...
So, Konori, what are
you doing up here...?
No, don't tell me.
You've come to warn Kurozuma
about the comprehensive sweep
that's happening tomorrow.
Let's go, Konori.
This isn't the
place for you.
You have to know that.
Yeah you're right.
This isn't the place
for me anymore.
I realize that...
but do you know
who helped me
figure it out in
the first place?
It was Kurozuma.
It's too dangerous!
Please don't go!
I understand
how you feel...
but I can't very well
abandon Hebitani.
Even when it's obvious
you're walking into a trap?
About that talk
we had earlier.
I have to tell you,
I really don't think
this is the rooftop
where you should be
leaving your name.
Sorry, Mii.
He's gone.
By the time I arrived
on the scene...
And here I am...
Back up on this
roof again.
But... you can still leave.
You have to think
this through.
You're a senior
Judgment officer now...
That means it
isn't right for you
to let criminals get away...
-Shouldn't you be...
-Yeah...
that would be wrong,
wouldn't it?
You came.
It's really been
two years, huh?
Hard to believe...
After it happened I
woke up in a hospital...
From there, I was sent to
a treatment facility...
and I didn't get
out of there
until about six months ago.
All this time...
I never...
It's still nice
up here, huh?
I thought I would never
get to see the view
from this roof again.
I also thought it
would be better
if I didn't see you
again, either.
-I know what you'll say.
-What?
That it's stupid for you
to go in on your own?
Like you did last time?
I'm the one who first
created Big Spider.
I should be the one
to bring it down...
Not Antiskill.
No, don't go!
You haven't
changed at all...!
You're still putting
others before yourself,
no matter what the
cost might be to you.
I couldn't stop you
last time. But now...!
You're the same way,
aren't you?
That's why you're
standing here right now...
Well... you should
really get going...
Go on...
She's just standing there,
waiting patiently for you.
So long.
Try to cherish the place
where you belong now.
I'm coming with you...
I... I can't go
through that again.
Enough already Mii.
Just let it go...
It's not like it
was last time, okay?
For either of us.
What used to be has
nothing to do with it!
The place where I belong
may have changed,
but the way I feel hasn't!
-Can I ask you something?
-Hmm?
Time's gonna pass, right...?
And we're bound
to change some.
But do you think some
feelings may stay the same,
no matter what?
I think if your feelings for
somebody are strong enough,
then they don't change,
even if you do.
Instead...
Those feelings keep growing
with every day you live...
Past and present
mingle together
to make you who you are.
The past and
the present...
It may sound presumptuous
but in the short time
we've known each other...
I feel like we've
built something
that isn't going to fade away
just because we get older.
I see.
We're friends no
matter what...
and we're going to keep
building on that friendship
every day.
You know what, Kuroko?
I have a small
favor to ask of you.
We are preparing to
launch a general sweep.
Target is District
Ten, Area G,
also known as "Strange."
Move out!
You two again?
Why are you here?
Wh-?! Hey!
What are you doing?
There.
Now that's what
I'm talking about!
You brought my armband.
But how did you...?
You know, Konori...
I think that
look suits you.
You're certainly busy for
this hour of the morning.
I've come to put
an end to this.
Him again...!
The guy from before!
Why, you little...
I'm sure you know
this already,
but I have a talent
for fighting.
Yeah... I know how good
you are in a fight...
but then...
Espers are pretty good at
fighting, too, aren't they?
And they've proven no match
for our numbers and weapons.
Hold it!
Mii...?
You're looking good today.
Is that you, Konori?!
Hebitani.
You've become
quite the scumbag
since the last time we met,
haven't you...?
Relying on your
minions and weapons
to win your battles for you.
Please...! You dumb brat...
You don't know anything!
You turned your back on us
and joined up with Judgment.
Go on...! Show these two just
how much we're capable of!
Hello there.
I'll be happy to stick
these into your bodies
if that would be quicker.
Esper...! Hah...
we've still got our ways
of dealing with you!
Oh, yeah?
You mean that thing?
You didn't really think
we'd fall for the same
trap twice, did you?
You must be stupider
than you look.
Kill the girl!
Y... you can't be serious...
but that's the
Railgun of Tokiwadai!
I said kill her!
If you wanna live, you'd
better follow my orders!
I want you two to
stay out of this.
Please, respect your
elders for once, okay?
Go on... do it!
Come on, boys...
This is sad.
You've gotta put
some heart into it...
or else it won't
be a challenge!
I'll be taking that...
and this, too.
You don't need a
stun gun, do you?
Hey, how...
So that's your
ability, is it?
Feels good to use it, huh?
Sure does.
I'm not gonna let you
have all the fun, though!
Now then...
what'll it be?
You really think you've
beaten us, don't you?
You're wrong...
Take a look at this!
Dynamite?!...
Who uses something that
old school anymore?
Go on. I dare you
to come closer...
I'll blow us
all sky--high.
Well? What's the matter...?
Are you scared now?
What a pain.
No... stay back...!
I'll blow us up.
Ah, Hebitani...
We had some good times
together, didn't we?
Stand still...!Not
one step more!
We all used to hang out,
just because it was fun.
What happened to that?
Stay there.
Stop.
What happened to you?
What changed?
I... I had no choice...
What else could
I have done?
This is the only place
where we belong...
I had to find a way to
keep Big Spider together...
and that could only happen
if I became Kurozuma.
And that's why...
I have no choice but to get
rid of you once and for all!
Hebitani...
This isn't where
you belong.
Your place is wherever
you can be yourself.
Haven't you
realized that yet?
Well... I'm glad
that's over, at least...
Now...
Here.
Mii...
Wataru Kurozuma ...
On behalf of Judgment,
I am placing you under arrest
for suspicion of assault.
That looks good on you.
I have to say...
It does look a little
tight in the bust area,
if you know what I mean.
Yes, well. That's because
I drink it every day.
When it comes to milk...
It's gotta be Musasino!
There he goes,
talking about breasts,
just like he was before.
And somehow, it's
still not offensive.
Kurozuma...
Thank you.
[Music]
The breeze up here really
does feel incredible,
don't you think so?
Oh, so that's it, Sissy.
I was wondering why you wanted
to come all the way up here.
Oh, look.
Somebody's scrawled
graffiti on this railing.
"Mii... Kuro."
Wonder what it means.
It means that
no matter what,
there are some feelings
that don't change...
It means someone cares
about someone else.
Academy City at its best.
I'll never forget the things
you showed me, Kuro...
The soft caresses, the
twilight strolls, the...
Hey, what's with this?
That didn't happen!
We call that payback.