Hot, hot, it is
so hot in here.
Come on, wake up...!
Please, open your
eyes, Sissy!
Sissy!
Wake up already...
Okay, well maybe a
kiss will help, then...
This isn't a fairy
tale, ya know.
But it did work.
You're awake
now, aren't you?
That's unexpected...
Why are you
two still here?
Yeah, well, there's
something we needed to ask you.
I find it unbelievably
hot in here...
It's the middle of summer.
Shouldn't they
at least turn on
the air conditioning for us?
You do make a good point.
I'm very sorry, but we had
a power outage last night.
Things haven't been
restored to normal quite yet.
All right, then...
They're using emergency
power for basic operations
and critical patients.
Again, seriously? !
Your solution to this is to
take off all your clothing? !
Well... it's really
hot in here, y'know?
We're not alone. There are
people everywhere!
What if I just leave
my underwear on?
No, not going to work.
All right.
Dr. Kiyama, we're really
interested in your opinion
on these patients
as a specialist.
I'd be happy
to help you...
but it's so hot in here.
Saten's running
really late.
Got on the blue
stripes today, huh?
In your email you said you
wanted to show me something.
That's right, and I
can't wait anymore.
This thing is
so incredible.
I've finally found
the elusive item
we've all been looking for!
Ta--da!
That just looks like
a music player to me.
It's what's on it
that really matters.
Just wait... I'll
show you later, okay?
Now, I'd like to pick up
where we left off,
if it's okay...
Why are swimsuits acceptable
and underwear is not,
when both expose the
same amount of skin?
No.... that
isn't the point.
This "Level Upper?"
Can you tell me what kind
of thing it is, exactly...?
What does it do...?
How is it used?
Unfortunately,
we don't know.
No details so far...
but it might have
something to do with the
students who have fallen
into comas recently.
That's what
you think, yes?
Right.
So... why bring this
problem to me?
Well, I've been giving this
some serious thought lately...
It seems that elevating
one's ability
might well disrupt
normal brain function.
If that's the case...
I think we'll need help
when we find this thing...
and I feel that your
professional experience
could be invaluable.
This is something I would
be happy to help with.
I am a
cerebrophysiologist...
it's my area... .
Aside from that...
there is something else
that's been bothering me.
Who are those girls?
Oh... so you're a brain doctor?
Are you here to look
at Shirai's brain? !
We are conferring with her
about the Level Upper matter.
Well, if that's the case-
This is pretty serious...
Anyone found in
possession of it
will be taken into custody.
Isn't that a bit extreme?
The investigation
is ongoing,
so I can't tell
you everything...
but it does seem that its
users suffer some side effects.
Anyway... I find
the users of any drug
usually turn to crime.
Saten, is there
something bothering you?
Oh...
no. Not at all.
I'm so sorry!
Please don't
worry about it...
It just got on
my stockings...
so once I take
them off....
How many times do
we have to tell you
not to take your clothing off
while you're in public? !
Look at me for a moment.
It's not like I'm anything
particularly special...
No man in here is going to
care about seeing my body.
Everyone has
different tastes,
so you can't really know...
Besides which,
it's not only men
you should be thinking
of, you know? !
I know you're busy,
so thank you for giving
us this information.
No... I thank you...
This has reminded me of the
time when I was a teacher...
I've enjoyed it.
I didn't realize you'd
been a teacher before.
I was once...
Bye.
I don't know what to say.
She's a little
different, huh?
Aren't you a little
different, too?
All right then...
I think it's time we headed
back to the office now.
That's a good idea...
and we should put whatever
data we have together
for Dr. Kiyama.
Yes, you're right.
Okay guys, so we're all
ready to head back
to the branch then, yeah?
Where did Sissy go?
I don't want to
give this up.
It's not like
I've used it yet.
So I don't have
to tell anyone.
But I worked so
hard to find it.
Are you okay?
Misaka...! Why are-
Well, you disappeared
so suddenly.
I was a little bit
worried about you.
Oh... it's nothing, really.
Are you sure?
Oh, well... It's
just that you know,
it feels like
everybody is involved
in this case
other than me.
I'm not Judgment
or anything.
Thanks you didn't
have do that.
You've always got that
thing hanging from your bag.
Yeah... I guess I do.
I got it from my mom.
It seems silly, huh...?
It's not as if good luck
charms are scientific
You're gonna be an esper,
Sis, that's so cool!
Sweetheart...
I need you to know...
I'm not totally on
board with this.
Mom's a big
worrywart, huh?
I'm just concerned
about her.
I don't want them
messing with her head.
It's not like
that at all, Mom!
I want you to take this.
A good luck charm?
That's not scientific!
No matter what happens,
you can always, always,
come back home...
I want you to know,
you're more important to
me than anything else.
At the end of the day, my
mom is just superstitious.
It's not like something like
this can protect me anyway,
right...?
It's not as if
it's magic.
It sounds like your
mom is really nice...
What I mean is, she
cares enough about you
to give you a charm
like that, right?
Yeah, she's a good mom.
But even still...
sometimes I feel like
I'm not living up
to expectations...
It's been all this time,
and I'm still only
a Level Zero.
Aw, Saten, really...?
Does your level
matter that much?
How is it going?
There's a lot of code
and jargon here,
so it's hard to
know for sure,
but I think
I've managed
to uncover some
sites that look like
they're Level Upper
exchange spots.
Good job, Uiharu!
A list of
presumptive places.
Wow, there sure are a lot
of them, aren't there?
Hey, what are you doing?
It has to be one of these
places, right...?
So, if I go through
them one--by--one,
I'll find it eventually.
Level Upper, huh?
It's everything
I've dreamed of...
Something that will
finally make me an esper.
But I don't know
anything about it,
and that scares me...
What if it isn't good?
You said you would
give it to me!
Where's the Level Upper?
The price has gone up.
If you want this, it's gonna
take another hundred thousand.
Could you just give
me my money back?
Please, just stop!
Quit whining and
give us the money!
Is he a test to see how
elevated your levels are?
Need to know how far
you've come, huh?
I should really call
Judgment or Antiskill.
Aw, great! My battery's dead!
Really...
what can I do...?
There are three
of them...
and I'm barely out
of grade school...
What can I possibly hope
to accomplish...?
I'm a level zero...
how can I help in a
situation like this?
You leave him alone!
Can't you stop?
He's already hurt...
and Antiskill will be
arriving at any moment!
'Scuse me... What did you say?
You've got a smart mouth
on you, don't you, kid...?
But you also don't
have any power...
so what right do you have
to tell me what to do?
You have power, so you
think you've earned it.
Well, I've got news
for you: you haven't.
So leave her alone...
You're a bunch of pathetic
losers with no power at all!
And I am an officer
of Judgment!
Shirai's here?
I'm placing you under arrest
for aggravated assault...
Now cooperate.
Ha...! You've got to
be kidding me, here!
One more little kid to deal
with isn't gonna a problem.
You should really
be more careful...
I've been running around
the city for hours already...
and then I finally find
what I'm looking for
and it's a bunch of thugs
assaulting my friend.
What are you
talking about?
It looks like I'm
going to be hazardous
to your health today.
Interesting... quite a skill.
Teleportation, huh...?
I never seen
that before.
It almost seems like
you're disinterested...
but you're very much
involved right now.
Before the Level Upper,
we used to be scared
of you Judgment types.
But there have been some
pretty big changes lately,
you see...
We're stronger.
And now that we've
gotten stronger...
we'd like nothing more
than to pound you
and people like you
into the ground!
Too bad you're
going to lose to-
He vanished!
He came from behind me.
He must've sneaked
up somehow.
I don't think I
have much choice!
I'm going to have
to use these on him.
I... missed him!
First I have to figure out
why I can't anticipate
his movements.
Yep, that was a different
direction than I expected.
That was pretty cool,
I have to say...
You cracked, what,
one, two ribs?
What do you think
you're doing now...?
Aw, don't tell me you
can't teleport anymore.
I'm not through
playin' just yet.
What, are we
playing tag, now?
It's fine if
you wanna run away,
but that means the
other two are forfeit...
the girl and the fatty...
I'll just kill them.
This building is scheduled
for demolition...
I probably won't be able
to find anywhere safe
to hide in here.
I don't hear anything...
no footsteps.
Okay... at this point,
he should still think
I'm on the first floor.
Ah...! Found ya!
Funny story: one
of our hangouts
happens to be
in this building...
so I know every last
little nook and cranny.
And in here...
sound resonates.
Hey, kid...
you heard what I said
about sound, didn't you?
You can spend all your
time tiring yourself out
and runnin' away...
I don't think it'll
take very long...
I'll get you soon enough.
Seems like you're finally
tired of playing tag.
All right, girl...
let's take care of this.
I kinda pity you...
Your life is going to
end before you even know
what ability
ultimately did you in.
I know more than
you think...
You have the
power to mislead
peoples' visual perception...
You distort the light
around you to make it show
what you want it to show.
You figured it out.
Your legs swing around
at an impossible angle...
Things I throw trace an
impossible trajectory.
Basically... you project
the image of yourself
to a different location.
So my focus is diverted
to a different area...
and my attacks end up
missing your actual body.
That explains it...
The pins I threw curved...
Because of you!
Heh... Enjoy.
I call it Trick Art...
So what now...?
How do you plan on
fighting against my power?
You have nothing to rely
on but your own eyes.
Perhaps...
Maybe what you
say is true,
and I can't hit you directly.
Huh? ... What are you
trying now, girl?
Here's the thing
about teleportation...
It means I have the
power to displace matter
from one place to another.
One example of this is
my ability to cut through
these steel--reinforced
columns with window glass.
Look, this is your
final warning.
Drop your weapon
and surrender...
If you refuse, I can't
guarantee your safety.
Give up...?.. Are
you kidding me...?
I'm not the one who
should be surrendering here.
It's sad really...
I wish our situation
didn't have to be this way.
But unfortunately you're
leaving me with no other option.
You should say
your prayers...
'Cause at this point...
I'm afraid I have no
choice but to crush you...
your little light trick
isn't going to
save you this time.
What the hell d'ya
think you're doing?
Do you know what will
happen after I destroy
all the columns that are
supporting the building?
You can make a
guess, can't you?
You wouldn't...! No way...!
You can't do this! ! !
I was a little worried
I may have overdone it a bit,
but... hah...
it was scheduled for
demolition anyway,
so I guess it's
no big deal.
Now... I'll be taking that
Level Upper from you. 'Kay?
Aw, do you wanna cry?
We can go demolish
some more buildings
if you would like.
Are you kidding me?
The best you can do is
hand me a music player...?
Please, don't
be ridiculous.
But the Level
Upper, it,
it's a song!
Wha-what did you say?
That's some good work...
We'll take over from here.
Gosh... I'm so glad
Shirai is safe.
I feel this way...
but I'm not proud.
She's a friend...
She's my age...
We are so similar
in so many ways,
but she happens to be
Levels up from me...
and it hurts a
lot of the time.
How can a Level Zero
relate to an esper...?
I wish I knew.
Ruiko!
Hey! ...
How's it goin'? !
Akemi? ... And Mu...
and Mako, too!
What are you doing
here alone, studying?
Yeah, I guess you
could say that...
What about you guys?
Just studying
at the library.
We can't change
our ability levels,
but we still have to
keep our grades up.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, hey guys, have
you heard about this
Level Upper thing?
Hold on what are
you talking about?
Oh I know...
It's the thing that's supposed
to increase your ability.
Yeah, yeah...
and I heard someone
say that it goes
for a lot of money
on the black market.
Well, I don't
have any money!
Um... hey, you guys...
I have one...
you know...
I've got one of them.
[Music]
Maybe I was
trying to pretend
I was okay with not
having an ability.
And maybe I was wrong...
Saten...! Please, no!