Give me a break!
I can't believe they
still have me training
with the green recruits
after all this time.
I didn't join Judgment
to spend time
doing pushups with
a bunch of newbies.
Come on, Uiharu!
Can't you even do one?
Here, would you
like a sip of this?
Wow. An entire year, really?
You've already been in
Judgment that long, Shirai?
So, I guess they
must be letting you
go out in the
field by now, huh?
Yeah of course they are.
How exciting.
That's kind of out of the
question for someone like me.
I'm not very athletic.
I've always been
a straggler.
And I was hoping that if they
accepted me into Judgment,
it might help me
to change that.
But what use is it if I can't
even keep up with the training?
You must always follow
your convictions
and act in the way you
feel is right at all times.
That's one of Judgment's
primary philosophies, you know.
If you can just
nurture the strength
to stick to your
convictions,
the results you seek are
sure to follow in time.
Let's see here.
Where else do we need to
get these cameras installed?
Right over there.
And there, too, I think.
It's almost shameful.
I really can't believe
they've put off the installation
of additional surveillance
cameras until now.
The Judgment officers at
this school must be pretty lax
to have let this happen.
Well, at least they're
taking care of it now
before any real
harm is done.
That's not the point.
It's the principle of the...
Come on. Let's go!
Right!
Seriously?
Right out in
broad daylight.
At school and in front of
Judgment officers, too.
You can't go
out there alone.
You have wait a minute
for backup to arrive.
Don't worry,
I can handle this.
You stay here.
I'll be fine.
All right, that's as
far as you're getting.
Huh?
Judgment knows
your crimes now.
I am arresting you.
The charges are destruction
of property and burglary.
Please be careful.
There may be more
than one burglar.
Please, that doesn't
really matter.
Car thieves are
small potatoes.
They're easy to deal with.
Now, if you would please
come along quietly.
Cooperate and no harm will...
Shirai!
Hey! Let's get going!
Right.
Wait! Please, stop running!
Move it!
Uiharu?
Uiharu!
Uiharu! Shake it off! Get up!
Oh, good!
I... I think I'm all right.
My goodness.
I think that took a year
or two off of my life.
What about the burglars?
They'll be long
gone by now.
My word.
You know, Uiharu,
today's further proof
you're not ready to be a
full--fledged officer.
You should stay back.
Just sit at the
branch office
backing me up like
you always have.
But that's not fair.
I did try to help you.
I told you that you
should be careful
because there might be more
than one of them in there,
but you totally ignored me and
now they've gotten away!
You're always doing this,
again and again.
You're reckless, and you try
to do too much on your own,
even though it keeps
getting you into trouble.
You ... you're exaggerating
things a little, aren't you?
When have I ever rushed
into a situation on my ow...
The better question would be,
when have you not?
You're always doing it!
Like just now.
You could've waited for...
I suppose you think it would've
been better to stand there
and let the
criminals get away?
Would you stop and think
about what you've done?
If you keep this
kind of behavior up,
what will become of
the promise we made?
The promise?
You mean you
don't remember?
Well, uh...
Oh, never mind!
If you don't even care,
I won't bother
helping you anymore!
Just do whatever you want!
How're you doing?
Is Uiharu around today?
Oh, you're here again?
You can't just stop by to
hang out whenever you want.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
But I have a legitimate
reason this time.
See?
A bona fide school
assignment.
I was going to see if
Uiharu would help me.
Ah, geez.
Fine, she's
right over there.
See?
So, you know, it might
not be the best time.
She's in a pretty
foul mood right now.
U--i--ha--ru!
We've got clovers
today, huh?
Where's the lucky
four--leaf clover?
There must be one here.
Hey! I'm lifting
it up even higher!
My, what a nice view!
Something's wrong.
What is the
matter with her?
She got into it
with Shirai a bit,
so she's a little off.
Wow, that sounds like
quite an argument.
It was pretty ugly.
We should probably
just leave her alone
for a little while.
I can see how that might
make her think about
leaving her post at
Judgment altogether.
Whoa, hold on there.
Let's not give her
any crazy ideas.
Together with Antiskill,
Judgment is in charge
of maintaining peace and
safety within Academy City.
It's not the kind of job
you can just toss aside.
Oh. I see.
But is giving her time
alone really all we can do?
There's more between those
two than meets the eye.
So, I think they'll
work it out somehow.
Huh?
What do you mean there's
more between them?
Well, you see...
I can't take it anymore!
If this fight is really
bothering you so much,
why don't you go ahead and
make up with her already?
Don't want to.
You need to do something.
Talk to her.
Otherwise, she's going
to stay angry with you,
and your partnership
will fall apart.
Maybe that's just
how it has to be.
If it ends over
something like this,
it wasn't much of a
partnership to begin with.
There's that bravado
she mentioned.
It isn't just bravado!
You and Uiharu have such
different personalities.
How did you become partners
in the first place?
Well, it's a long story.
It wasn't something I
had planned on happening.
She was so slow she could
barely keep up in training.
But then one day ...
Okay. That concludes
our patrol for the day.
If you have any questions,
now's the time to ask.
Actually, there is
something I'd like to ask.
What is it?
I've been a
member of Judgment
for an entire year
at this point.
I'm always stuck doing
research and odd jobs,
or I accompany you
when you go on patrol.
It's not what I expected.
You're upset because
you're an honor student,
but you're not being treated
as a full- -fledged officer,
right?
I don't know if that's how
I would put it, exactly.
I thought that
maybe it was
because I'm still in
elementary school.
Your age isn't the only
cause for concern.
There's another issue.
You've shown a lot
of potential so far,
but you have a habit of trying
to solve things by yourself,
and that's dangerous.
You have to learn to rely more
on other people around you,
or you could get
yourself into trouble.
Come on, don't
make that face.
Tell you what, why don't I buy
you something sweet as a reward
for all your hard work?
Just hang on one sec while
I withdraw some cash.
I knew it. She does still
think of me as a child.
Hello, Shirai!
What a coincidence!
Uiharu? What are you doing
in the Seventh District?
Middle school
is almost here,
so I came to look at
the different schools
and dormitories.
Middle school, huh?
You have an older friend?
Why would you say that?
I'm looking for my own sake.
It's such a big decision.
Oh, uh--huh.
She's the same
age as I am?
I always thought she was
two or three years younger.
So, Shirai, have you decided
which school you're
going to go to yet?
Oh. Yeah, I have.
It's this place called
Tokiwadai Middle School.
What a great opportunity!
Tokiwadai is one of the
five most prestigious schools
in Academy City!
I bet life at a place like
that is so refined and elegant!
It may not actually
be as glamorous
as you're making
it out to be.
I bet everybody
is pretentious.
All the students who are
enrolled at the school
are at least a
Level 3 Esper.
Basically, it's going to be
full of a whole bunch of girls,
all of whom are convinced that
they are somebody special.
From what I hear,
there's even a Level 5 there
who they've given the
absurd nickname "Railgun."
I can only imagine how arrogant
and condescending a girl
like that is going to be.
That's a pretty severe
assessment of someone
you've never met before.
So, if you came to
look at schools,
what are you doing in here?
Is something the matter?
Excuse me.
Is something going on?
That man over there.
He's focusing on
where the workers are
and what they're doing.
I don't like looking
at people's things
without their permission,
but I'll have to
make an exception.
I don't see anything
too out of place.
He has a gun in
his right pocket.
He's robbing the place?
I'll go inform
the employees.
I want you ready to
lead the customers out
if it looks like something
bad is happening.
You're not going
to arrest him?
Of course not.
That would be out of bounds.
That's a job
for Antiskill.
They're the ones
who catch criminals.
How can she be so
complacent about it?
That's correct.
Contact Ant...
No one try
anything funny.
Everybody keep quiet.
There's no need to
make a big scene.
Damn, he's already
making a move.
This is what I've
been training for.
What do you know?
That wasn't so
difficult after all.
Pathetic.
Letting a little girl like
that get the best of you.
You're useless.
Uiharu!
What's that? So this other girl
is a friend of yours, huh?
That's very convenient.
Easy, now. Stay
right where you are.
You're with Judgment,
aren't you?
A Judgment officer could
never abandon a hostage, right?
Especially if she happened
to be a friend as well.
Could this get any worse?
If so, they should
come out now.
What are they thinking?
Sounding the alarm
is going to spook them.
Do they care more about the
money than people's lives?
Security signal received.
Proceeding to
eliminate intruder.
Please drop your weapon
and lie down on the floor.
Gimme a break.
There's something
in his right pocket.
Warning issued.
Initiating action.
Close one!
Konori, no!
Don't charge someone.
Not unless you
can be certain
of what they have
up their sleeve.
Remember that, okay?
-Konori!
-Hey!
So, there were more
of you hiding here.
Are you okay?
He was an idiot.
Did you think you could
take me so easily?
Please, stop it!
-Shirai!
-I'll show you.
Are you all right?
Please don't hurt her anymore!
Shirai!
There's no one to
blame but myself.
I made a reckless decision
without thinking things through.
It's my fault.
I put them both in danger.
What a mess I've made.
Konori was right about me.
This is more trouble
than I'd bargained for.
Please!
But still.
Just give up already.
No.
You don't have to do this!
Please!
If nothing else,
I can get you out safely.
What now?
What are you up to, kid?
I'm free?
You're a teleporter?
Are you still
in there, Shirai?
Why didn't you come?
Why did you just send me?
I'll teach you
to mess with me.
Shirai, get out of there!
Come on, hurry!
Unfortunately,
that's not an option.
My power is not
yet at the point
where I can transport myself.
And besides,
I intend to see this case
through to its conclusion.
Say something!
Somebody! Help!
This is an emergency!
There's a burglar inside,
and he's attacking
a Judgment officer!
He's got her trapped!
Is anybody listening?
I need help!
I bet I can guess what's going
through your head right now.
You're thinking the alarm
sounded a while ago.
So, surely Antiskill will
be here any minute now.
And, if you can
just stall me
and prevent me
from taking hostages,
everything will be okay.
I'm right, aren't I?
You're wrong, though.
Because I don't
plan to wait around
to be taken into custody.
The power of "Equal Speed."
Anything I throw will
keep moving forward
until I release my power.
It doesn't matter
what's in the way.
All obstacles
will be destroyed.
Too bad for you.
Didn't see that
one coming, huh?
Time's running out.
Hey!
Use your power to get
the money out of there.
If you cooperate with me,
I'll let everyone else go.
Yeah. I know.
You and I should
become partners.
Working together
we'd be unstoppable.
So, what do you say?
This situation just
keeps getting worse.
I acted impulsively.
And I've dragged
everyone down with me.
But... It's not over yet.
My answer is ...
No!
I'll never work
with someone like you!
Be your partner? Please!
You're a petty thief
who couldn't even manage to
rob a small place like this
without making a mess
of the whole thing.
So, I think I'll pass.
Anybody! Please! Help me!
I've already made my decision.
I believe in the
power of justice.
And I'll never
stray from that!
Well, then.
That's too bad.
His ability may be strong,
but it isn't especially fast.
As long as my
legs cooperate.
That means I'll
have to kill you.
Aw, sorry.
Did you think I could
only throw one at a time?
Hey!
Your power versus my power.
A steel ball versus
teleportation.
Shall we see which
is the quicker one?
Damnit.
You know, that was
pretty amazing!
It takes real skill to handle
something like that by yourself.
Yeah.
What exactly
happened there?
If it's okay, I'd like
to make you a promise.
I will always follow
my convictions
and act in the way
I feel is right,
just like you told me.
And, like you, I believe
in the power of justice,
and I won't stray from it.
No matter what happens
I'll never lose heart.
Someday, I know I'll be as good
a Judgment officer as you are.
Thanks, Uiharu.
I'd like to make a
promise to you, too.
Until today, I thought I could
take care of everything
without anybody's help,
but I was wrong about that.
I propose a partnership
between the two of us.
Let's become full-fledged
Judgment officers together.
Deal!
Aww.
What a sweet story.
Hmm? Is something wrong?
Oh. No, it's nothing.
That must have
been the promise
she was talking about.
But how am I going to
apologize to her now?
Hello? Shirai, here.
Huh?
Uiharu did what?
Well, she figured out
where those car thieves
you lost track
of earlier were.
As soon as she did,
she rushed right out of here.
After what happened,
she's determined to find them.
So, Shirai, what are you
going to do about it?
I am going to...
Follow your convictions
and act in the way
you believe is right,
never straying
from justice.
That it?
Go on.
You can still
work together.
Even if you do
butt heads sometimes.
Hey! What are you
dawdling around for?
If you keep moving
at this rate,
the two of us will never become
full--fledged officers together!
Always in such a hurry.
A happy ending.
I'm not too surprised.
Fights don't tend
to last very long
when you're that young.
Sh... Shirai,
don't you think we should
slow down a little?
Forget it.
I'm going on ahead.
Hey! No teleporting!
That's not fair!
It's about time for
Judgment to step up.
You think this
job is easy?
Let's see you try it.
There's an idea!
Next episode,
"Sissy's First Time"!
You don't have to
say it like that!