This is true.
The events I'm
about to describe
actually happened to
our friend's sister's
roommate's boyfriend.
It was a sultry
summer evening,
and this boyfriend of hers
was strolling through a park.
There was no sign of
anyone else in the area.
A lone woman appeared
and came up to him
asking how to get
the train station.
The boyfriend was
a polite young man,
and he graciously began
giving her directions.
As he did, the woman
stared at him
with a vacant
look in her eyes
and started slowly
lifting her hands.
Then, suddenly, there
was a great whoosh!
Why was there a whoosh?
The strange woman
removed her blouse.
Please! That was the
least scary story ever!
We did a lot to create
a creepy atmosphere,
but I don't think anything
can save that story.
Huh?
It really happened
to someone we know.
How is that not freaky?
The legend of the
Undresstress who disrobes
without warning!
No, not scary.
It's more like a
story about a sicko
who could use some
serious therapy.
Then how about
another one?
This site is full of
different stories.
"When you see the wind
turbines spin backwards,
it's a sign of
the apocalypse.
Doom is just
around the corner!"
"Don't cross
between districts
at four--forty--four
in the afternoon.
You'll find
yourself in the
Imaginary Number
School District!"
It says there's the tool
that'll instantly increase
your ability-
The Level Upper!
This is getting
ridiculous.
Would you stop looking at
that stupid site already?
Urban legends are useless.
They have no basis
in scientific fact.
This is Academy
City after all.
Geez, you have no
sense of adventure.
Besides, sometimes these stories
are based on real events
that have just
gotten twisted
until they become
crazy legends.
Look at this one.
"The boy with the power
to prevent other powers
from working."
That's a story you'd only
hear in Academy City.
The power to prevent
other powers from working?
That's the most absurd
one we've heard!
Nobody could have
that ability.
Please! Don't you agree, Sissy?
Yeah, totally crazy.
But if someone like
that did exist,
I'd sure like
to fight him.
But, of course,
he doesn't. So ...
Even more urban legends, huh?
A boy who somehow
has the power
to prevent other
powers from working.
Of all things.
We got ourselves
a cutie here.
Oooh, and she's
from Tokiwadai, too.
Wanna come with us?
Have some fun tonight?
We'll even take you
back to your dorm.
Of course, there's no telling
how late it might be by then.
What do these
idiots think
they're going to accomplish
by talking to me?
Pathetic.
Everyone else is
pretending not to see.
It's not that
they don't care.
They just can't do
anything about it.
If they interfered, they'd
only get themselves hurt.
And that wouldn't
help anyone.
Everyone has to look
out for themselves.
That's the way it works.
And if there is somebody
out there who would jump
in the middle of this
to help out a stranger.
Well, that person
is just a fool.
Oh, hey! There you are!
Thanks for keeping
her company, guys!
You shouldn't wander off like
that. You know how much I worry!
Okay! Thanks, again!
You mind telling
me who you are?
Why couldn't you
just play along?
The plan was I pretend
to be your friend
and casually walk
you away from here.
And now that's ruined!
Why should I follow
a convoluted plan
from some random guy?
Who do you think
you are, punk?
Think you can make
us look like fools?
Yeah, dude, you got some
kinda problem with us?
-Well, do ya?
-No, I just ...
What's the use, really?
Yeah, I've got a problem.
You guys don't have
any shame, do you?
All of you ganging up
like this on a single,
helpless young girl?
It's pathetic!
I mean, have you taken
a good look at her?
She's basically a kid.
You heard her
talking to me.
She sounded like a child
who hasn't learned
how to respect her elders.
She looks sweet, but she
still hasn't outgrown
her rebellious phase.
That's how young she is!
And besides that,
you can't even face
this defenseless child
unless you gang up on her?
You guys make me sick!
You wanna know what's making
me sick right now, Wonder Boy?
You are!
I just can't
understand it.
Why don't my
shocks work on him?
Could it really be like
that urban legend says?
No, impossible!
If I hit him with my full
force, he'd be toast.
Next time I run
into him, I'll-
Let's see here.
Can you remember any
landmarks or anything?
Landmarks?
Hm. Well, there was a crosswalk
in front of it, I think.
That's not really
a landmark.
There are kind of
a lot of them here.
It's you!
Oh. Hey, Bug Zapper.
What's up?
Don't call me that!
I'm Mikoto Misaka!
And today is the day I'm
gonna settle the score with you!
Okay, that's nice.
So does that mean you
aren't busy right now?
If it's time you want,
I've got plenty to spare.
Good deal.
Then do you think you
could help this woman
find where she
parked her car?
Huh?
Yeah. I know I parked it in a
lot around here some place,
but I can't figure
out exactly where it was.
Uh, hold on.
Why me?
Well, there's somewhere
important that I need to be now.
You've got time, so
it's fine, right?
No, actually,
it isn't fine!
You want to weasel
out of this,
but I'm not going
to let you!
And don't try to come up
with some lame excuse again,
because it isn't
going to work.
Wow. It sure is hot out,
don't you think?
What ... what are you
doing that for?
I've been walking around
in the blazing sun
for quite a while now.
I'm dripping with sweat.
What is with this woman?
I have no idea. I just met
her a few minutes ago.
Anyway, lady, would you
please put your shirt back on?
That woman is
being assaulted!
Huh? Is that boy ripping
off her clothes?
-I think he is!
-No, really.
Huh?
You've got it all wrong!
Hey, get back here!
Excuse me ...
If you're going to run off,
could you at least
give me my shirt
back, please?
Whatever, hurry up and
put it back on, okay?
People are
starting to stare!
That was refreshing.
I feel so much better now.
What's the deal
with that woman?
Just randomly stripping
her clothes off in public?
Huh? It really happened
to someone we know.
How is that not freaky?
The legend of
the Undresstress
who disrobes without warning!
No way, that was
just a story.
-Hello?
-Hey, Sissy!
Where are you right now?
Are you busy?
I was about to go have
tea with Uiharu and Saten.
You're welcome to come
along if you'd like.
Well, the thing is,
I'm stuck helping
out this weird lady.
Weird? How so?
She started stripping off
her clothes without any warning?
She's stripping! It's the
Undresstress. It has to be!
Oh, no, Misaka!
Will you be okay?
Let go! Please!
Could you two try
to get it together?
Text me her picture,
okay? I want documentation!
Get a grip, you guys.
Don't go thinking she's
something from an urban legend.
She might seem
a little odd,
but I'm sure she's
just an ordinary----
You said somebody is odd?
Is it me you're
talking about?
No. Of course not.
I mean, you did
take off your shirt.
Well ...
The number you have
dialed is unavailable.
Please leave a
message at the tone.
That seems a little bit
suspicious, don't you think?
Shouldn't we
track Misaka down
and make sure
that she's okay?
You're really taking this
urban legend seriously.
How incredibly childish.
To thank you for
keeping me company.
Oh, all right. Thank you.
Why something hot?
Especially curry soup?
Most people don't
realize this,
but when it's hot out,
a warm drink is
better for you.
Also, curry contains
special spices
that help to relieve fatigue
and rejuvenate the body.
I think I understand the
theory of what you're saying.
But, emotionally,
I find a cold drink
on a hot day more
satisfying, so ...
Emotionally? Huh.
I suppose when
you're younger,
emotions tend to
drive your decisions
more than practicality.
I'll get you something
else. What would you like?
Oh, no. Please, that's okay.
The sentiment is enough.
Sorry about that.
I tend to look at things
from a logical perspective
maybe because
of all the time
I spend doing research.
You do a lot of research?
Are you some kind
of scientist, then?
I'm a cerebrophysiologist.
My primary area of study
is AIM diffusion fields.
Diffusion fields.
Those are the weak
spheres of power
that Espers
continuously emit
without being
consciously aware of it?
That's right. You've already
learned about them in school?
Uh--huh. Back during
my first year.
They told us the
fields are so weak
they can't be detected
with human senses
and have to be measured
using specialized devices.
I'm especially interested
in discovering ways
to harness and
apply that power.
Oh, does that mean ...
Do you know a lot
about Esper abilities?
Are you interested in
something specific?
Well, yeah,
um ... Is it possible
that there's an ability
that can negate
other powers?
Well, there are so many
different abilities out there.
Can you give me a
clearer example of
what you're describing?
Let's say someone was hit
with an electric shock
and it had no effect.
An electric shock, huh?
Maybe this person
generated something
to act as a lightning rod
and deflected the
electrical current?
It's something
different than that.
I'm not really sure
how to explain it.
Is this person an
acquaintance of yours?
Oh! No!
It's an urban legend my
friends were talking about.
It's ridiculous. I shouldn't
have said anything.
An urban legend, huh?
Is that the
kind of thing
children are interested
in these days?
I know it sounds silly,
but there are quite a
few of them going around.
Y'know, like the
Undresstress?
No, never mind. Forget
I even mentioned it!
Oh! I'm so sorry!
No, don't worry about it.
It'll wash off
easily enough.
Can't you keep
your clothes on?
Still no answer.
Why can't I get
a hold of her?
Probably 'cause the
Undresstress is attacking her!
I'm not listening
to that nonsense.
Look what I found.
This website has a ton of
detailed information on it.
And it's all about her.
Let me see.
What is it? What does it say?
It's terrible.
It says here the victims
of the Undresstress
may try to hold out,
but all eventually
utter a final cry
and are lost forever.
This gets more
absurd every second.
It's just a dumb story.
But, if you're
that worried,
remember that Sissy
is the ultimate,
unstoppable shock princess,
the Ace of Tokiwadai.
She's hardly going to be
undone by some strange woman
just because she likes
to undress in public.
That's not all.
I think something even
more terrifying
could be happening here.
Now what are you
going on about?
What if the Undresstress
is contagious somehow?
What? You mean
like a disease?
Maybe those who meet her
become cursed the way she is.
Maybe they become
Undresstresses, too!
Then Misaka will go around
stripping for everybody!
Oh, no. That can't happen.
Not to my Sissy!
No! Don't do it,
Sissy! You can't!
Um, Shirai?
Uiharu, you have to find
a way to lift the curse!
Right now!
Please, don't get so
worked up. You're hurting me!
Yeah, remember?
It's nothing but an
urban legend, right?
Sorry for inconveniencing
you so much.
Well, I've already
come this far.
There you go.
Great. Thank you.
Oh, yes. Thank that young man
for me, too, won't you?
Young man?
He's a friend
of yours, right?
He could tell I
was in trouble
and asked what he
could do to help.
Oh, did he?
He's a good kid.
He's always butting in.
I think he just likes
to play the hero.
He barges into the
middle of a situation,
babbling random stuff,
and then disappears again.
It's annoying.
I don't know how
to describe it,
but something about him
rubs me the wrong way.
He's headstrong and naive.
It's like he stepped
out of a fairy tale.
He's always convinced
that he's...
He sounds like a fun guy.
So are you, you know,
in love with this kid?
What? You're crazy!
You know what I'm
talking about.
That thing where you
pretend to hate someone but,
really, you're
nuts about them?
What do they
call it again?
Let's see, here.
Ah, yes. Playing hard to get.
That's it.
That's impossible!
What's happening?
Why'd the alarm go off?
No time to ask questions.
Come on, let's go!
Move.
Thanks so much
for helping me.
Take care, okay?
'Kay. Drive safely!
Come to think of it, who forgets
where they parked their car?
There's definitely something
off about her, all right.
I'm exhausted.
It's not like I did
all that much today.
Why am I so worn out?
This is his fault.
He ruined my day.
Next time I see him
I swear I'll...
They all broke!
A week's worth of
breakfast, just gone!
This is awful.
I waited in line
for two hours!
I can't believe it! This
is why you ran away earlier?
You saddled me with some
crazy exhibitionist lady
so you could go shopping?
You know, for a student
as poor as I am,
getting groceries
while they're on sale
can be a matter
of life and death!
Not that somebody from
Tokiwadai would understand!
I didn't have an awesome
day either, thank you!
Her skirt got dirty,
so she stripped again,
and I had to wash it,
and after all that,
she told me
I was playing...
What?
Never mind.
Just forget about it.
You owe me a fight!
I don't get why you're so
eager for another fight.
You've lost every one
so far, haven't you?
Shut up!
I haven't been giving it
everything I've got yet,
so I haven't
lost anything.
Okay. How are we going
to resolve this?
Huh? Well, it's a
simple matter, really.
I just have
to beat you up.
Quit with the sighing,
already. It's irritating me!
All right, I give.
If it's the only thing
that will satisfy you.
I'm willing
to take you on.
Good. I'm glad you
finally came around.
We shouldn't bother
anybody if we fight down here.
I'm ready when you are.
So bring it on.
You don't have
to tell me twice.
I've been waiting a long
time for this opportunity.
All right, here we go!
Like I thought. Shocks
don't work on you.
Well, then ...
Huh? What's that thing?
Whoa! Hey, now.
Isn't it against the
rules to use weapons?
Not if I made it
using my ability.
The iron sand vibrates, making
it sort of like a chainsaw.
Fair warning, it might
hurt a bit if it touches you.
I'm really not
okay with this.
Do you think you could
put that thing away?
You can dodge and duck
and run all you want.
No matter how far you scamper,
I can still reach you!
It's longer!
Gotcha! Let's see
if you can dodge this!
He deflected the sand
particles back at me!
Oh, well. I
anticipated that, too.
Well, looks like
that's the match, huh?
Oh, no.
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
Uh--oh. Even in the wind
she can control it?
No matter how
many times you try
it's going to end the
same way it always has.
I've got you! You can
stop my currents in mid--air,
but...
My electricity!
It isn't even flowing!
How does this guy do it?
Uh ...
Yeah. I give up.
You're the winner.
Jerk! Don't screw with me!
Take this fight seriously!
I'm trying to help.
You looked really scared!
No I didn't.
You don't scare me!
Now you're lying!
Your eyes got all red
and watery like a baby.
Then you flinched.
Die!
Get back here!
Be careful! If that
had hit me directly,
it could have killed me!
You know full well it
wouldn't have hurt you!
Whether it would have
worked on me or not,
you've gotta be pretty
sick to send an attack
like that without
even hesitating.
I'll have you know
I've never used that much
of my power to attack
somebody before today!
Then why start now? Why me?
Quit running like a
little girl and face me!
Just leave me alone.
I didn't ask for this!
Hey, I'm back.
Huh? Kuroko isn't home yet?
I'm exhausted.
So, it's true then.
Kuroko? Where are you hiding?
You were stripping
off all your clothing.
Saten was right.
You really were cursed
by the Undresstress!
Here!
It's imperative that you put
these on your head immediately!
Geez. What's gotten
into you now?
This is the only way
to lift the evil curse.
The curse of the
vile Undresstress!
Undresstress,
I banish you!
Put those down! Have
you gone insane?
I banish you!
Curse, be gone!
So, she's the Level 5.
I've heard so
much about her.
What a fascinating
young girl.
I had fun today,
and as an added bonus,
I get to do the preview.
Let's see.
I think I'll
accompany the preview
with some tasteful
disrobing. Next time...
Don't you dare!