[Music]
You're not
getting away now.
Hey, hold on just a
second. I'm only...
You might as well give up!
Hey, Misaka!
Oh, Uiharu. Saten.
Hi, guys.
What's up? Did
something just happen?
We heard a loud noise
from this direction.
Eh?
No, it was nothing.
[Music]
Today is a very
important day.
It's me and Sissy's
anniversary.
It happened exactly
one month ago.
Fate bound us
together as roommates.
I ordered
something special.
Unfortunately it
hasn't arrived yet.
But I still have
one thing to offer.
Me.
A heartfelt anniversary
present gift--wrapped
in nothing other than ...
My birthday suit!
Kuroko!
-What?
-Sissy! You're home at last!
-We're here.
-Also!
I can't believe
I'm in her room.
This is too amazing!
It's so stylish.
Talk about chic!
Come and feel this.
The bed's so
soft and fluffy.
-It's very comfortable!
-This is incredible!
Seriously, opening
the door like that?
What were you thinking?
I didn't expect company.
Why did you bring
Uiharu and Saten along?
I happened to run into
them out on the street.
They tagged along with me
while I did some shopping.
Then they said they wanted to
see my dorm, so here we are.
-Shopping?
-Huh?
Just for a little.
It's official!
The girls' dorms at
Tokiwadai are amazing!
I'm green with envy!
And don't forget
the dining room.
It was absolutely
gigantic!
It's not all
that wonderful.
Sissy, why did you choose
today of all days?
My perfect anniversary
plans are ruined!
Oh! But what if ...
I wanted you to witness
this special day.
Exactly one month ago,
fate bound Kuroko and me
together as roommates.
We may be two people,
but we share a single heart.
And so Uiharu, Saten,
I truly hope we have your
blessing on our anniversary.
Here's looking
at you, kid.
Shall we drink?
Um, excuse me, Shirai.
But are you all right?
Oh yes, I'm very
well, thank you.
I'm afraid we don't have much
to offer by way of hospitality,
but please make
yourselves...
Hey, Saten. What are
you doing down there?
Well, when you visit
a friend's home,
it's natural to do some
good--natured snooping,
don't you think?
Hot stuff!
Stop that, Saten!
You can't just go through
other people's things!
Just what I'd expect
from you, Misaka!
Well, as a matter
of fact...
Those actually
belong to me.
Those are your
panties, Shirai?
These make a very
bold statement.
I would hardly consider
those to be bold.
They're a simple
necessity.
Every lady should have a
pair of black panties.
Well, what about
this pair, then?
Those really
lift the spirit.
I wear them when I
need some cheering up.
And what about this
barely--there thong?
Handy for avoiding lines
when one's clothes
fit very tightly.
A.. And this black mesh,
full--body stocking type--thing?
That's absolutely essential.
It brings out
the supple feline
that hides in the
heart of every woman.
Couldn't you have at least
given me a little warning?
Sorry, I was feeling
overwhelmed.
I needed something to
calm me down a little,
and seeing your ordinary striped
panties helps me to relax.
I don't see what
the big deal is.
It's all just underwear.
And there are other kinds
that you haven't
even gotten to yet.
A pearl--white babydoll
with an open bra
and feminine frills.
A lace teddy with
sexy garter belts.
And also these.
That's good to know.
At least she wears
regular underwear, too.
It's very comforting.
I was beginning to
think I didn't know her.
Sorry.
These are actually mine.
As for you, Kuroko!
Explain yourself!
What is my underwear doing
under your bed, huh?
You've got it
all wrong, Sissy!
Oh, you know what would
be awesome, Misaka?
I'd love to see some old
photo albums if you have any!
Great idea! So would I!
Maybe some pictures from
when you and Shirai
were in grade school?
That would be so
interesting to see!
Wow! How adorable!
Is that from your first
day of elementary school?
That pretty woman next to
you-is she your mother?
Uh, yeah.
What a cute kimono!
You were such a
darling little kid!
You know, I'm a
little surprised.
About what?
It's just-you're this
powerful Level 5, Misaka.
The Ace of Tokiwadai,
an electromaster.
I guess I kinda expected
you to be one of those kids
who get taken away while
they are really young
and immediately
fast--tracked for success.
It wasn't like
that at all.
I wasn't always like this.
I started out as a Level 1.
I was just an
ordinary girl.
Wow.
Cool, let's look at
Shirai's photos next.
I'd be glad to
show you them.
At least, I would be if
I had something to show.
Unfortunately, I don't
have any photo albums
for your viewing pleasure.
I am a girl who believes
in seizing the day.
I don't like to
dwell in the past
nor do I worry
about the future.
No, not me.
I stay in the present
and savor each moment.
That's the philosophy
I live my life by.
What about this?
No, you can't
look at that!
Kuroko, you...!
It's a good thing
that you like to live in
the present moment so much,
because right now
I'm thinking
you're not going to have
a very enjoyable future!
You've got it all wrong!
Don't you understand
I only made it
because you mean
so much to me?
Do you not even remember
what an important day
it is today, Sissy?
And here I thought you
brought Uiharu and Saten
so they could
celebrate with us!
What?
Celebrating with
Uiharu and Saten?
Oh, I see what
you're saying.
Then you do remember
what today is, Sissy?
Of course! How silly of me.
Today is the one...
week anniversary
of the day you introduced
me to Saten and Uiharu!
It's unbelievable!
The last seven days have
gone by so quickly!
It seems really crazy that
it's only been a week!
It feels like we've known each
other so much longer than that.
Don't you guys agree?
I'm really glad I
met you two, though.
Why does she treat me
so much differently
from those other two?
I'm starting to feel like
I'm a third wheel here.
We've already been
through a lot together.
Like this little bean.
It's been cast aside and
neglected by its fellow beans
and now it is but a
sad solitary legume.
You know, this is
better than I expected.
Yeah?
That's the liquid sandwich?
Anyway, like I was
saying, Uiharu...
Please, Saten, don't
finish that thought!
You guys're hysterical!
Pipe down, would you?
What's with all
the slurping?
Red beans have feelings
too, you know.
Huh?
Can't you see how
I might be feeling
a little abandoned, here?
Well, uh ...
One week since
you met them?
Don't make me laugh.
One week is nothing.
One month.
That's how long it's
been for us, Sissy.
Today is the one--month
anniversary of when fate decreed
that we would be
bound together!
One whole month, Sissy.
Exactly one month ago,
by some random chance,
you and I became roommates.
Since then, we've eaten
together and slept together.
Shared each others'
joys and sorrows.
All right here!
In this very room!
But you, you don't
remember, do you?
She seems upset.
It does seem serious.
Maybe we should go and
leave them to talk.
-Kuroko, stop that.
-What is it, Sissy?
You know full well that you
manipulated your way in here.
It wasn't fate or random
chance or anything of the sort
and now you talk about joys and
sorrows and lonely red beans?
You know, I think I just
remembered something urgent
that I need to attend to.
How dare you make
this all sound like
some kind of fairy tale!
I was just altering the
story slightly, that's all.
And in return, I'm going
to alter your face for you!
Maybe I see things
different than you.
It's not like I'm
asking very much.
I just wanted to
celebrate today with you
in one small way, Sissy.
Yes?
I have a delivery.
It's addressed to a
Miss Kuroko Shirai.
-Is this room two--oh--eight?
-Yes.
Can you tell me what
the delivery is?
It just says
"computer parts."
I shouldn't have
been so worried.
These people know
their business
well enough to be discreet.
What's the name
of the sender?
Ehh, Love and Herbs Premiere
Aphrodisiacs, Limited.
Way to throw discretion
right out the window!
Kuroko, why does this small
celebration you have planned
involve the use
of aphrodisiacs?
-Well, uh ...
-I've been too lenient.
It looks like you're going
to need some harsher punishment
before you learn
to behave yourself.
Now I'm going to fry you
until your appearance
matches your name!
Did you forget that I can
just teleport away from you
whenever I want to?
If this is how
you truly feel,
you leave me no choice.
You will not return the
love I freely offer.
So I'll make sure nobody else
can have your love, either.
Is something wrong, Sissy?
Dormitory Rules, Part 9.
The use of Esper abilities
inside the dormitories
is strictly prohibited.
Surely you haven't
forgotten that, Shirai. Hm?
Good afternoon,
Head Resident,
and might I say you look
quite stunning today.
Naturally, we haven't
forgotten the rules.
We weren't just casually
using our powers.
I assure you,
we had a good reason.
Yes, a very good reason.
Is that so?
There were unavoidable
circumstances, were there?
Yes, that's it exactly.
You see, we...
Too bad.
Kuroko!
If I made allowances for every
so--called emergency situation,
the dorm would fall
into utter chaos.
Rule breakers must be punished,
without exception.
That's how order
is maintained.
Don't you think?
Y...
Yes.
Give me a break!
Why should I be stuck
doing this, too?
So I got a little
carried away.
It was no big deal.
This punishment
is unreasonable!
Making me clean this
whole pool by hand?
That's cruel and unusual
by anyone's standards!
Ahhh!
We started in the morning
and it's already
past noon now.
How is it we're not even
a third of the way
done with this yet?
I don't think we're going
to finish it all today.
I totally lucked out!
Here with Sissy
at the pool,
spending quality
time alone together,
working up a good sweat.
This is the perfect opportunity
to get some payback
for yesterday's humiliation.
You know, Sissy ...
When working
under a hot sun,
rehydration is essential to
one's health, don't you think?
Would you like some of this
specially formulated beverage?
Thanks. I'll pass.
Why not? Aren't you thirsty?
Well, tell me this.
Those computer parts
that you ordered,
they didn't happen to find their
way into that drink did they?
That's what I thought.
Shirai?
Yep. That's Shirai, all right.
We thought that was you,
but what are you
doing down there?
What does it look
like I'm doing?
I'm scrubbing
out the pool.
We see that.
But why?
Because we live in
a cold, cold world,
even during the summer.
What are you
two doing here?
We're members of
the swim club,
so it's our job to check
on the tank filters.
They must be Kuroko's
classmates.
And that means ...
They're actually
younger than me.
Hey, Sissy.
I want you to meet some
classmates of mine.
That's Kinuho Wannai
on the right
and the other's
Ma'aya Awatsuki.
Hey, nice to meet you.
-And this august personage...
-Excuse me.
I think I recognize you.
Are you Misaka?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
That's me.
I knew it!
Do you remember me at all?
You came to my
rescue a while back.
Some guys were
giving me trouble,
and you dealt with them
like they were nothing.
It was amazing!
Did I do that? It must
have slipped my mind.
Anyway, ever since then,
I've really wanted
to say thank you.
I've heard a lot of
stories about you.
It's an honor to
meet you in person.
That sounds like my
Sissy, all right.
She goes around dealing
with thugs like that
no matter how many times
I tell her not to.
No doubt.
When it starts to get hot,
the weirdoes come out
of the woodwork.
It sounds like you
were incredible.
Absolutely.
You were so cool and
collected the whole time.
No, no, no. It wasn't
a big deal, really.
Wait a sec...
Oh, you guys
are hysterical!
Déjà vu! No, it's
just my imagination.
The incident yesterday
is making me paranoid.
I'm not the
odd--man--out here.
That would be crazy! Right?
Hot as it is, it must be
tough working out here.
I should have a sports
drink in my bag
if you'd like some.
Here, you need
it more than me.
I'd love some.
That's so nice of you.
Why is she excluding
me like this?
Could it be?
Now that I think about it,
this isn't the first time
she's ignored me lately.
I've tried over and over again
to deepen our friendship,
but she keeps
tossing me aside.
It's entirely possible
that Sissy has been deliberately
giving me the cold shoulder.
Suck it up, Kuroko.
You've lost your
confidence,
and you need to get it back.
Forget your anxiety and
play to your strengths.
That's it!
I'm a teleporter,
after all!
There are any
number of ways
I can prove my
worth to Sissy.
I just have to
find the right one.
Wow, incredible!
It's washing away
all the grime.
My ability is manipulating
water currents,
so it's a piece of cake.
We need to finish up our
inspection right now,
but after I've
taken care of that,
I would love to come
back down here
and help you out, if you
wouldn't mind the company.
Huh? I don't know...
It's the least I
can do to repay you
for saving me
from those guys.
Well in that case,
how could a girl say no?
Excellent.
I'm so glad you agreed!
It's amazing!
We'll be done in no
time at this rate.
Thank you so much!
Okay, then. I'll
see you in a bit!
I'll leave the sports
drink here, too,
so you can stay hydrated.
Have as much as you want.
Wow. Those friends of yours
are really nice, Kuroko.
One could say so.
I'm glad they came along.
This will take ten
minutes doing it her way.
One could say so.
Ahhh!
When we're done I wanna
get some ice cream.
One could say so.
I've got a rip in one
of my school uniforms.
What do you think I
should do about it?
One could say "sew."
Is there something wrong?
You seem down or something.
I'm fine. Pay no
attention to me.
Don't trouble yourself
on my account.
I'm a useless teleporter
who can't even clean pools.
Um, Kuroko.
If there's something
that you need to get
off your chest, then...
Thanks, but no thanks!
It's my own fault
for not being worthy of
your affection, Sissy.
I know I'm no help at all.
I just annoy you
all the time.
I see why you've been
acting this way.
Someone like me could
never hope to deserve
somebody as amazing as you!
Great. What do I do?
I don't know how to handle
sudden breakdowns like this.
I'm curious.
I wonder if Misaka's
given it to her.
I don't know, but I sure wish
we could be there when she does.
It seems only fair
since we were with her
when she bought it.
I'm interested to find out
how Shirai will react.
I mean, given her taste
in underwear and all.
Yeah, that was crazy, huh?
I never would
have expected her
to own all that
daring lingerie.
But, you know, it's the
thought that counts, ultimately.
Yeah, that's true.
So, Kuroko.
Do you remember what happened
exactly a month ago today?
-A month ago today?
-That's right.
Don't you remember?
The night that you
broke into my room?
The Head Resident
caught you,
and you got a
good scolding.
Then, the next day
they made the two of us
clean the whole dining hall.
And one thing led to another,
and here we are.
Still together
a month later.
So, if we were going to
have an anniversary
then it would be today,
wouldn't it?
May I open it now?
Yeah, of course.
I plan to be friends
for a long time,
so don't quit on me now.
Do you mean it, Sissy?
A long time?
Like, forever
and ever, maybe?
Well, of course I mean it.
We go to the same school,
and we live in the same room.
We couldn't split
up even if we tried.
After all, we're
partners, right?
Here.
Here's to being partners.
Shall we drink?
Here's to being forever
bound together by fate!
Here's to remaining
roommates and good friends!
All right, then. What do you
say we get back to work?
Right. Back to work.
You know something, Sissy?
I think it would be
better to wear a swimsuit
while you clean the pool.
That way it wouldn't matter
if you got wet, you know?
Yeah, but it would
be too much of a pain
to go back and get it.
Actually, I thought something
like this might happen.
Ta--da!
I brought your school
swimsuit with me
in case of just
such an emergency.
The last time I checked,
that swimsuit was in my locker!
You should know locks don't
mean very much to somebody
who has my
particular abilities.
Now, why don't you go
ahead and put it on, Sissy?
Hey!
How sad. I don't think I've seen
such childish underwear before.
That's enough!
Give them back!
Like I said, put on your
swimsu-Wait a sec...
Oh, my goodness!
This is a bunny,
and this is a bunny, too!
We match!
Me and Sissy match!
Kuroko!
It sounds so lively.
What's going on?
Misaka, we're all finished
up with our inspection,
so we came back to help
out like we promised.
Oh, yes. Hit me again with
your electrified whip of love!
Give them back!
Give them back now!
-I can't do that.
-I'm dead serious.
If I give them back,
you'll stop.
Stop saying that!
Let's pretend we
didn't see anything.
Yeah. That's a good idea.
I'll never get
disheartened again.
Nothing can take
her from me.
We'll be together forever!
[Music]
He loves me,
he loves me not,
he loves me,
he loves me not ...
Um, excuse me.
Please stop doing
that, Saten.
That's not what the flowers
on my head are intended for.