Computational device?
By using the AIM diffusion
field as a medium,
I was able to
construct a network...
and by distributing
the processing
across multiple brains...
I can enable complex
computations...
That's what the Level
Upper really is.
But why?
I requested the use
of Tree Diagram...
I needed access to it to
perform certain simulations...
but for whatever reason,
I was denied.
I needed a computational
device in its place.
You've used their brains
to construct a computer?
I've put about ten thousand
of them together...
That should be an
adequate substitute.
Don't give me such
a reproachful look.
It will all be
over soon enough.
And once it is,
everyone will be released.
This is a treatment program...
It will uninstall
the Level Upper.
I'm giving it to you.
There are no lasting
aftereffects.
Everything will
return to normal,
and nobody will be
lost in the process.
And I'm supposed
to trust you...?
You give me this thing
that probably hasn't
even been tested before,
and I should just take it
without asking questions?
You have quite a
harsh view of me.
Yes. Dr. Kiyama is
not at this location.
Copy that...
We are seizing all data.
What is all this?
That's not good.
It looks like they've
already arrived.
It hasn't been long enough
since they lost
contact with you
for that to be the reason
they're making this move...
They must have figured
it out some other way.
I programmed my equipment with
security measures in the event
it was booted without
following designated protocols.
Those measures have
been activated,
which means all data on the
Level Upper has been lost...
The only means of waking
the sleepers now
is what you're holding
there in your hand.
So take good care of it.
Attention, Harumi Kiyama!
Antiskill is here, huh...?
One thing that I
can say for them
is that they
sure move fast
when their orders
come from the top.
You are under arrest
for suspicion of distributing
the Level Upper...
Surrender yourself at once.
What are you gonna do...?
It looks like this is the
end of the line for you.
The Level Upper
is a program...
It was designed for making
computing equipment
through the use of
human brain activity...
but that isn't all.
It also generates a certain
byproduct within its users.
I've got an interesting
demonstration for you.
[Music]
I want you to slowly place
both hands behind your head
and lie down
on your stomach.
The girl hostage
appears unharmed.
Secure her!
What was that?!
I... I can't control myself!
Impossible...!
She's an esper?!
Keep the change...
and please, get out
of here quickly.
Why? What's happening?
Kuroko, tell me
what's going on!
Kuroko!
Antiskill managed
to locate Kiyama,
but she's engaging them...
What's more...
She's using an ability.
What are you saying...?
Is she an esper?
The databank doesn't
show any record of her
receiving any
ability development.
Even so...
She is clearly using
some kind of ability ...
And what's more,
it looks like
there have to be multiple
abilities in play.
No way!
No one ever has more
than one ability.
There are no exceptions,
are there?
Maybe it has something to
do with the Level Upper.
In her system, she
has ten thousand espers
synaptically linked
by some kind of bizarre
computer network...
They can be thought
of as one giant brain.
If she can really
control them,
she should be
able to do things
that no normal brain
could do alone.
If my guess is correct,
then Kiyama's become
something entirely new.
The phantom being
that nobody thought
could actually exist...
A compound esper...
"Dual Skill."
Antiskill's wiped out...
All of them.
Uiharu!
Are you all right?
You can relax.
She just caught
an aftershock
from the fighting
and got knocked out...
Her life is in no danger.
Mikoto Misaka ...
One of only seven Level
5's in Academy City...
Despite your extensive
skill and experience,
I doubt you have fought
against an opponent like me.
Do you think you'll
be able to stop me
when I have the power of ten
thousand minds at my disposal?
That's what you
want to know...?
Can I stop you...?
Of course I can!
You're full of surprises.
You really can use
a lot of different abilities,
can't you...?
This "Dual Skill" thing's
pretty fascinating...
It should make for an
interesting battle.
You'll find my ability is
different in nature and in name
than the impossible
power people speak of...
It should be called...
Multiskill.
Call it whatever you want,
for all I care...
A new name won't change
what I'm going to do to you!
Is something wrong?
You knew I could use
multiple abilities,
but you didn't think I
could use them all at once?
Is she insane...?
She wields those abilities
without any concern of
getting caught up in them?!
That was anticlimactic...
I would've thought
a Level Five
would be capable
of more than that.
So you were able to counter
one of my shocks...
Don't think that
means you've won!
Huh?
Oh, crap!
Why don't you stop
this foolishness?
There's just one
little matter
that I need to look
into further...
and once that's done,
I'll release all of them.
I won't sacrifice anyone.
Are you kidding me?!
You won't sacrifice anyone...?
What about all the people
you've dragged into this?
What about all the people whose
lives you've toyed with...?!
After all you've done
there's no chance you're
getting away with it!
Good grief.
You may be a Level 5
but still,
you have no idea
how the world
works, do you?
Not the twisted
world you live in!
You undergo a special
"ability development"
on a daily basis.
Do you really think everything
they do in this city
is safe and humane?
The powers that be in Academy
City are concealing something
very important about
these abilities.
The teachers who work here
know nothing about it.
But they're still
"developing" the brains
of their young
students every day.
Can you begin to understand
how dangerous that might be?
I'll admit that's quite an
interesting story you just told.
And I'll be sure to take a
nice, long look into it.
Once I've taken
you into custody!
That will have to wait...
I've got other things to
tend to at the moment.
Empty cans...?
Gravitons!
So, what will you do now?
That's easy...
Blow them away!
That's very impressive...
Too bad.
Well...? I made
short work of those.
Are we done ye...
I expected you to give me
more trouble than that...
Is that really
all you've got?
Level 5?
I suppose you'll
hold it against me.
Look at that...
I caught you.
Impossible!
You used magnetics to
make yourself a shield.
I'll shock you at
point blank range.
It didn't work against
this idiot I know...
but I don't think even
you possess an ability
as out of this
world as his is.
Too slow!
I admit, I did hold
back on you a little.
-Teacher?
-Teacher!
-What the-...?
I'm hearing this
directly in my head.
Teacher!
-Am I...
-Teacher!
am I hearing Dr.
iyama's memories?
Teacher?
I must have created an
electrical circuit between us
that allows me to hear them.
Teacher!
Hi, Miss Kiyama!
Me, a teacher?
This must be some
kind of joke, right?
Not at all...
Why, is there a problem?
You do have a teaching
certificate, don't you?
Yes.
In that case what could
be out of place about you
taking up a position
as a teacher?
That certificate's
just something I happened
to get along the way.
I know research is
your preferred area...
I'm not asking
you to give it up.
Far from it in fact;
I'm asking you to head up
a high level experiment
that's being backed by the
board of directors themselves.
You really mean it?
You see those
children down there?
They're what we refer
to as "Child Errors."
For whatever reason,
they were abandoned
here in Academy City...
They have no other family.
Ah...
They are also the subjects
of this experiment...
as well as the students
who you will be teaching.
In order for the
experiment to succeed,
we will need to keep
detailed growth data
on each one of the subjects,
analyze them meticulously,
and make any necessary
adjustments as time goes on.
I'm sure you can see
that having their
teacher handle
that will save a
lot of trouble.
I guess so.
It does sound
more efficient.
Uh... my name is Harumi Kiyama
and starting today I'm
going to be your teacher...
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you,
too, teacher!
This is not gonna be easy.
Ha--ha...!
She fell for it!
We got the Teacher!
Hey, you two!
Are you okay Miss Kiyama?
Yeah... It's a sunny day.
This shouldn't take
long to dry outside.
You can't change
your clothes out here!
Boys! Look away, right now!
Seriously, you can't do that
in the middle of a classroom!
Aw, gimme a break.
It's not like we'd be
interested in a flat chest
like that anyway.
Me...? Flat--chested?
I hate children.
They have no decency.
You're not really
very pretty, Teacher...
Do you have a boyfriend?
Wh... what was that?
Didn't think so.
But I'll be your
boyfriend if you want.
They have no manners.
And if you'll just
look at your books...
They play stupid pranks.
I see that you're sad...
If there's something
bothering you,
I'd be happy to listen.
They're far too emotional.
Hey...! You
can't be fussy.
Eat it all!
They're overly familiar,
and they become
attached too quickly.
I really hate children.
Edasaki.What's wrong?
Oh, Miss Kiyama!
I slipped in the
rain and fell.
My apartment isn't
far from here...
Would you like to wash up?
You mean it?!
Wow! A bathtub!
Is taking a bath
that exciting?
Yeah. At my facility, we
only get two showers a week.
So... can I really use it?
Yeah.
Hooray...! I'm gonna
brag to all the others!
Teacher?
Do you think if I
tried really hard,
I could make it to
Level 4 or even 5 someday?
At this stage it's too early
to know one way or the other.
Do you want to be a high--level
esper when you get older?
Well, of course.
I mean, who wouldn't?
But Academy City's going to
all this trouble to raise me.
I'd like an ability
that would help the city
in return, you know?
With all this work,
I have no time for my
research anymore...
Teaching is a real
pain in the neck.
On top of which....
I hate children.
They're indelicate,
annoying, and loud.
Hey, Teacher... will you
be my girlfriend, please?
Yeah, whatever.
They have no manners.
Yay!
They play stupid pranks.
-Oh... is that me?
-Mhm!
They're far too emotional.
It's a surprise
party just for you!
Happy birthday, Teacher!
-How old are you now?
-Aren't you surprised?
Do you like
the decorations?
What did we say?
You have to eat it all.
Right.
I knew you could do it!
Children are...
You'll feel a
slight prick.
Anything unusual here?
No, no problems so far.
We're fine, too.
Okay, great.
Are you frightened?
Not one bit. After all, you're
in charge of this experiment,
aren't you?
I completely trust
you, Teacher.
Do I finally get to stop
playing teacher now?
Dopamine levels
are dropping!
Anticholinergics are
having no effect!
Hypovolemic shock is
setting in from the burns.
Lactated Ringer's solution.
Transfusion, stat!
There's nothing
more we can do.
Uh... Hurry and
contact the hospital!
No... we won't do
anything of the sort.
But if we don't do
something right now...
Are you a
scientist or not?
Don't get frantic, just
gather all the data you can.
I'm ordering you to keep this
experiment strictly in--house.
Everything was completed
here without any incident...
Nobody saw anything
out of the ordinary...
Understood?
Y... Yes, sir.
Don't worry you did your job
and you did it well...
It is a pity this had
to happen to them.
But that's how scientific
progress is made, after all.
You don't need to worry yourself
about this little accident...
I'm still expecting great
things from you in the future.
What was that?
You saw what they...
we did?
Half the street's
been blown away.
It's Misaka!
What...
What were they doing?
On the record
or off of it....?
Officially, it was designed
as a test in controlling
AIM diffusion fields...
but... the real study...
was on the effects of
pushing an ability
beyond its natural limit.
They over--stimulated the
children's AIM diffusion fields
in order to study runaway
abilities first--hand.
Then...
They were intentionally
manipulated
to run out of control...
but I didn't realize
what was going on
until after it happened.
Experiments...
on the children.
Innocent little kids...
And even after
all this time...
they still
haven't woken up.
We stole their youth from
them, and for what...?!
To turn them into
laboratory rats?!
But...
If something that
terrible happened,
why didn't you report
it to Antiskill?
23 times.
That's how many times I
requested to use Tree Diagram...
If I could just
get access to it,
I could use it to find
a way to revive them...
I could run simulations
to uncover the true
cause of the accident.
Tree Diagram is the
greatest supercomputer
in Academy City...
If I'd had it, I could have
brought those children back...
I could've set them free
to laugh and run
and play in the park
like children
are supposed to.
But I was always
turned down...
twenty--three times,
they said "no"!
Don't you get it?
The board of directors
was in on it!
There's no way
Antiskill would act!
There must have been a
better solution than this!
You understand nothing!
I would do anything
to save them...
anything in the
entire world!
The whole city can
hate and revile me.
I don't care!
I'm not going to let
anything stop me now!
Hey... what's wrong?
The network...
it's out of control.
Oh, gosh... what's that?!
A fetus...?
[Music]
I'm putting a stop
to Kiyama's scheme...
I will find a way to save
Saten and the others...
But what is that thing?!
Nobody said anything
about fighting a monster!