Hello there, Haru'ue.
Your friends are here.
You said my
friends were here.
You mean Uiharu
and the others?
Well, why don't
we just see?
It's... Banri?
Yes! It is you!
Incredible!
You're here.
I can't believe it!
I need to tell Uiharu
about this right away!
[Music]
So, the ten child subjects
who've been missing
are now securely installed
at MAR's laboratory?
Yes.
They've been
found, finally.
Isn't that great, Uiharu?
Oh... yeah.
And the woman responsible
for the Level Upper incident
is behind this
situation as well.
She said that she didn't care
if the city was destroyed,
so long as the
children were saved?
That's a pretty extreme stance,
wouldn't you say?
So, Therestina said she's
going to find a way
to wake up Edasaki
and the others?
Huh?...
Oh... yeah.
Well, then, it sounds like
we've closed the case.
Excellent work!
Is something the matter?
It's nothing.
I know you all
too well, Sissy.
I'm guessing you're still
concerned about Kiyama,
aren't you?
You still aren't convinced
it was the right idea
to have the children
taken away from her, right?
I'm just not sure.
Well, be sure.
You made the right choice.
At least that's what
I believe, anyway.
Right.
Even so.
You crossed the line
this time, Sissy!
Going into a place
like that on your own?
If anything had
happened to you,
I don't know what
I would have done!
Hello, there.
You're spacing out now.
-Are you okay?
-Oh... yeah.
Come on. Aren't you anxious
to see how Haru'ue's doing?
Well.. yeah... I guess.
She'll be thrilled
to see you!
Let's get a move on!
Hey! All this pushing
isn't really necessary!
Now, now, you don't want
to keep her waiting, do you?
Let go!
Thrilled to see me, huh?
Well... maybe I should
bring her some things.
Let's see here....
Snacks, a game,
some reading material...
And what else?
Changes of clothing,
of course!
Waiting isn't good
enough anymore.
I need to start
looking for her.
Oh, Haru'ue.
I'm so proud of you.
I would do anything
to save them.
anything in the
entire world!
The whole city can
hate and revile me.
I don't care!
I'm not going to let
anything stop me now!
I'm sorry, Doctor.
-I don't have anything yet.
-I.. um...
Oh, it's you.
I have this friend, Haru'ue.
Maybe you've already
heard of her by now.
I actually haven't known
her for very long.
But she did tell me that she
and Banri Edasaki were friends
when they were little.
And.. you see...
Haru'ue is a telepath.
Every time one of the
poltergeisting
incidents occurred,
she could hear
Edasaki's voice.
Because of the
way she acted,
she was suspected of
being responsible.
Even so, she did
everything she could
to hear what Edasaki
was saying to her.
But now Edasaki isn't
missing anymore...
so...
Surely...
Surely, Haru'ue
must be happy
with the way things
have turned out.
So, what are you
trying to say?
I don't really know.
I just thought I
should tell you.
I was so close to
finishing the vaccine
that would help them...
All I needed was to get my
hands on the First Sample.
I could have gotten their
runaway abilities under control.
I could have awakened
them at last.
I could have
brought them back!
Dr. Kiyama.
Let's collect all of your
data and take it to MAR.
It's bound to
be of some use.
And then they'd let us in to
see Edasaki and the others.
I couldn't possibly.
I know that's
what you want.
Let's go see them!
How can I say no to that?
Wow, you came all
the way out here
to bring me your research?
That's right.
Although... we
were also hoping
we could see how the children
were getting along here.
That's not possible.
We had to transfer
the children.
They will be going to a
facility that's better equipped.
Okay. Which facility?
I'm sorry, but I can't
disclose that information.
You'll just have
to take my word
that they'll be
well taken care of.
From here on out,
MAR will be responsible
for their treatment.
And another thing.
Haru'ue will be
staying with us.
What?... But, why?
Well, as you know,
she's spent a long time
waiting to see
her friend again.
She wants to
stay by her side.
Really?
Here, pick one.
Um... one, what?
Why, a color...
If the color you choose
is the one that comes out,
I'll let you see
Haru'ue and the others.
-Well... um...
-So indecisive!
Well, why don't
we choose yellow?
Here.
Aw, it's a brown one.
What a shame, huh?
This is no time to
be playing games!
Oh, I'm not playing
at anything.
Uh-oh... I'm so
sorry about that.
I don't understand.
What's going on?
Oh, well. It's not as if the
data will be of any use anyway.
Director Kihara,
it's about time.
-One moment.
-Kihara...?
Oh, you mean you
didn't know that?
That's my middle
name, you see.
Kihara.
In full, Therestina
Kihara Lifeline.
Why, you...!
Dr. Kiyama!
Are you okay?
Say something please!
We're terribly busy,
you understand.
I hope you won't mind
if I ask you to
show yourselves out.
Here, have some tea.
You seem to be
in a good mood.
Well, why wouldn't I be?
It's a relief
to have the
poltergeisting case
closed, finally.
We can go back to our
everyday lives again.
Uh-huh...
I know you guys have been a
little bit out of sorts lately,
but now everything can
get back to normal.
Isn't that right, Shirai?
I haven't behaved any
differently than usual.
Here.
I know! I'll give
Uiharu a call
and see when Haru'ue is
getting out of the hospital.
It is practically
the height of summer.
We should enjoy it.
You're right about that.
Hey, Uiharu.
It's Saten.
Where are you?
Saten...
What's wrong?
It's...
Oh...
Saten!
What's the matter?
Uiharu!
Come on, I can't understand
through all the sniffling.
What is it?
Finally, this is it.
I've finished gathering
all the material
about the poltergeisting.
Well, go ahead
and get rid of it.
I got a call from the
MAR laboratory just now.
They said they have all the
information they require.
Aw, man. This
took me so long!
Did they say
anything more?
Nope. They said
"it's over now"
and left it at that.
Doesn't that seem a
little... unusual?
Her name's Therestina Kihara?
Are you sure that's
what she said?
And Kiyama,
what about her?
I don't know.
She went... somewhere...
Take it easy.
It's gonna be okay.
Huh? Found her.
Yes, Therestina Kihara Lifeline.
Gensei Kihara's
granddaughter.
-Oh, my.
-What, is there more?
She's included in the personnel
data from Kihara's lab,
from the time he
wrote his thesis.
What does that mean?
Therestina was Kihara's
research assistant?
That would make
sense, wouldn't it?
Wait a second!
What is it?
Therestina was the
first test subject
for the ability crystal.
How can that be?
Whoa, let me get
this straight.
You're telling me Kihara's
first human experiment
was on his own
granddaughter
and that Therestina
helped with his research?
The same woman who
has the Child Errors
under her protection?
What's going on?!
Don't ask me! I'm just
as confused as anybody.
What... What do we do?
I can't believe it!
How is this happening?
Please try to stop crying.
I can't!
Haru'ue... Edasaki...
all the other children.
It's okay.
What now?
I've failed them all!
What do I do?
Tell me, how much longer are
you going to sit there, crying?
You.. hit me...
Isn't there something more
useful you could be doing?
When are you going to
get a hold of yourself
and act like a
Judgment officer again?
Let me take over.
If you want.
Checking for
probable locations
where the children
would have been sent.
Where's Misaka?
Sissy...
Here.
You can use
this to dry off.
Great, thanks a lot!
I can't believe Kongo's been in
the hospital this entire time.
It seems excessive.
Is her condition
really that serious?
I'm kind of
worried about her.
Maybe we should go
pay her a visit, then.
Yeah, good idea.
Ignore her.
Keep moving.
I should tell you.
The children were aboard the
trucks that passed by just now.
Don't you want
to go after them?
You tricked us.
Are you angry?
I want to know what
you've got up your sleeve.
You make it sound
so sinister.
You are Gensei Kihara's
granddaughter.
You were also the
first test subject
for the ability crystal.
Used as a lab rat by
your own flesh and blood.
And yet, you're
still assisting
with your
grandfather's research.
Using the children
as you were used.
So, tell me, what
are you planning?!
You've done your
homework, haven't you.
But what you still
don't seem to realize
is that I don't answer to
anybody other than myself.
Moron!
And now you're going to try
forcing me to reveal my plans.
That sound.
It's Capacity Down!
You're familiar
with it, then?
Why do you have it, though?
Why wouldn't I have it?
I am its creator,
after all!
You are?
As it happens, I gathered a
lot of helpful information
from loaning it out to
those idiots in Skill Out.
So this new version is
significantly more powerful.
Though that did require making
the device a good deal larger.
Apparently, even a band
of fools like Skill Out
can be somewhat useful.
-Stop screwing around with me.
-Huh?
Using Skill Out, too?!
They aren't your lab rats!
No need for hysterics.
I missed.
Calibration's a bit off
but I guess that'll just draw
the fun out a little longer.
Why, you...!
My power...
Poor girl. Haven't
you noticed that
none of your attacks
are reaching me?
Keep running,
my darling Level Five,
but it won't do
you any good.
Goodness. What on earth
is going on out there?
All that smoke.
It looks like a
disaster area.
Huh? Isn't that.
It's Misaka!
People like you
and your friends
are such fascinating
specimens.
In thrall to your own
naive sense of justice.
I owe you my gratitude.
It's all thanks to you
that I was able to track
down the test subjects.
As a reward, I'll let you
in on a little secret.
I needed access
to those children
because I intend to perfect
the ability crystal.
No... You... can't...
Oh, can't I?
Who's going to
stand in my way?
We've got a new candidate
for experimentation.
Someone take her away.
Just a moment!
I'll have you know,
that girl you're carrying
is a friend of mine.
And you do not
want to cross
Mitsuko Kongo of
Tokiwadai Middle School!
All units, report status.
Yellow Marble..
good to go.
Brown Marble.. good to go.
All units, you are clear
to proceed as planned...
This is Blue
Marble reporting.
-We've lost Railgun!
-You what?!
I apologize.
We're currently searching
the surrounding area.
-We'll find her.
-Never mind!
But I will not soon forget
today's incompetence!
Sissy!
Misaka! Are you all right?
How do you feel?
Are you hurt at all?
I'm confused...
What happened?
Well, I'm not one to brag,
but it all worked out,
thanks to me.
I'm certain you'd love to
hear all about my heroic rescue
but really, there isn't
that much to tell.
Oh, all right,
if you insist.
I'd hate to deprive you of a
thrilling tale of selflessness.
Really? So Kongo saved me?
Therestina.
Sit back down, Sissy.
You need to
rest some more.
Get out of my way.
I don't have time to be
lounging around in bed now.
I need to go.
I have to help
the children!
You're staying here, Sissy.
What a fool! I snuck into
the laboratory on my own
and lost my temper.
I found the children,
but I led Therestina
straight to them as well.
And now they're all gone.
They're gone,
and it's entirely my fault.
Don't you see?
I have to stop her
and make this right.
So stand aside, Kuroko.
What are you doing?
Misaka...
I want you to
stop for a minute.
Look around and
tell me what you see.
What are you
talking about?
I see you, standing there.
I'm sorry.
Really.
You're right.
I was... I was being selfish.
And... I've gone and caused
trouble for you all again.
It isn't any trouble.
Really. But I'd rather
fight together with you
than worry about you out
there all on your own again.
You know.
That's what friends
are for, isn't it?
Saten's right!
You're not alone.
You've got all of us!
Yeah, I know I do.
Thanks, you guys.
You're next, Uiharu.
You'll apologize to Shirai.
Tell her you're
sorry for the way
you've been treating
her through all this!
Hey, hold on!
That's not fair!
You, too, Shirai...
Apologize to Uiharu
for slapping her!
I'm sorry for
how I've behaved.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
So? Don't you have something
to say to me, as well?
Yes, I do.
Thanks, Kongo.
Oh, it was
nothing, really.
We now have
irrefutable evidence
that Therestina Kihara is
involved in illegal activities.
We've always suspected
there was something suspicious
about her organization.
We're looking
into her, too...
We don't have
any time to waste.
We need to be
doing something!
Can't Antiskill help out?
It isn't that easy
for us to get involved.
There are limits
to what we can do.
Oh, yeah? What about
finding the strength
to overcome your limits?
It's you...
from the workshop.
You're the one who said that
when you convince yourself
you can't do any more,
you're finished.
Well, we can't
give up. Not now.
The children need us!
Okay. Give me
a little time.
I'm receiving satellite
surveillance data
from Antiskill.
The MAR trailers are
on Urban Expressway Five,
just passing
the interchange
for School District Eighteen.
Urban Expressway Five.
That leads to District
Seventeen, doesn't it?
Why District Seventeen?
Do they have some reason
for heading there?
I think so.
Gensei Kihara had a
private lab in that area.
Well, let's see.
Here. Can you zoom in enough
to see what's
behind the trailers?
Sure.
Dr. Kiyama!
Geez, she's going
after them on her own?
How can she take
this all on herself?
Really, Sissy?
You know it's
almost impossible
not to say something
sarcastic now.
Yeah, it sounds like you've got
a lot in common with Kiyama.
Hey, now. That isn't true.
So, is there something I'm
supposed to be doing here?
'Huh?' Oh, are
you still around?
Here, wash it
down with this.
We can't fight on
empty stomachs, can we?
-Now eat up, everyone!
-Right!
Huh?... What is
this recording?
[Music]
All right, then.
Let's get going!
[Music]
We've got work to do!
We'll defeat Therestina...
-find Haru'ue...
-and Kiyama...
And then...
We'll save the children!