Uiharu!
Saten, are you all right?
That was a close call.
Are you injured...?
You're safe now.
I know that lady!
[Music]
Right... No one
was injured.
And, of course, we need to
make an official announcement
to keep any panic
from spreading.
As we know...
what happened wasn't the
result of an earthquake.
It was poltergeisting.
Yes... You're correct
about that, girls.
Bye.
I wanted to thank
you personally...
for saving my
friends back there.
I'm just relieved that
nobody was injured.
I was wondering something.
Are your people measuring
the AIM diffusion field
around this area?
Is MAR able to detect
abnormalities in the field
before an event happens?
I... well... um...
I mean, you arrived so
quickly on the scene.
Could you tell
me your name?
Yes... I'm Kuroko Shirai,
of Tokiwadai and Judgment
Branch One-- seven--seven.
That explains it.
It seems your
branch in particular
has some outstanding
officers working for it.
There is a connection
between AIM diffusion
fields and RSPK.
It's impressive that
you've already found it.
From what we can tell,
the RSPK incidents
are being caused by
someone tampering
with AIM diffusion fields,
and these
synchronized events
are leading to the
poltergeisting we've seen.
It would have been helpful
if you'd mentioned this at
the joint conference earlier,
that way I would have
known to be on the lookout
for any suspicious persons
in the area at the time.
That's under Antiskill's
jurisdiction.
I thought I was
clear before.
We want Judgment to focus
on countering rumors
and managing matters
of day--to--day safety
within the city.
Tampering with AIM
diffusion fields.
We know somebody who
has done just that.
Could this be
her work, also?
Whose work?
Misaka!
We're going to ride along to
the hospital with Haru'ue.
Oh... we'll come, too.
Unfortunately,
we can't do that.
The head resident will
be doing room check.
What a relief.
Thanks for
letting us know.
Goodnight.
She's gonna be fine.
They've all made it
safely back to the dorm.
So... Tell me, Sissy.
What has captured your
attention so completely?
The Level Upper fiasco?
Why are you
looking at that?
It's just a hunch I have.
There's something about
the current situation
that reminds me of it.
The manipulation of
AIM diffusion fields
was a big part of that
incident as well.
What's more...
I'm still not going to be
choosy about my methods.
If you don't like the
plan I come up with,
you'll have to come
and stop me again.
I see what you mean.
You're thinking that
Kiyama might be involved
in the recent spate
of poltergeisting.
I understand why,
but aren't you forgetting
one important detail?
The woman in question
is currently a resident
of the detention center in
School District Seventeen.
There's no way a high--profile
criminal like Kiyama
would be able to
get out of there.
Yeah, you're
probably right.
There is something
else about all this
-that concerns me, though.
-Yeah?
The way Haru'ue was behaving
at the fireworks show.
Where...?
Where are you...?
Please, where?
Yeah, you're right.
It's kind of like she
was talking to somebody
who wasn't even there.
All right, let's think
through the situation.
We know this is the result
of someone tampering
with AIM fields.
Which means it has to
be the work of an esper.
Wait, you aren't saying...
I know... It's a horrible
thing to think about.
I'll comfort you, Sissy!
Get off me!
How could something like
that even be possible?
Haru'ue only
recently transferred
into our school district,
remember...? Although.
You're from District
Nineteen, right, Haru'ue?
Weren't there several
poltergeisting outbreaks
in that area?
What was it like?
I think Saten's
onto something.
Poltergeisting incidents
in District Nineteen
have stopped completely
for a short while.
And, in the meantime...
here in District Seven.
That's a coincidence...!
You really think a
sweet little girl like her
could have anything
to do with this?
You're right.
There's no way.
It's my Judgment training
making me suspicious
of everybody.
It's just, after that
call from Konori, I...
Uh...
Hello, Konori.
I hope I'm not
disturbing you...
Oh, Shirai?!
-Are you okay...?
-Yes.
Why didn't you call
and tell me...?
You're always doing
stuff like this!
'Night, Konori!
I'm glad she's sleeping.
I'm sorry you had to
come all the way here
after the hospital.
Oh, please, don't
worry about it.
It's not like any of this
is your fault, you know.
Besides, if she's
your roommate,
that makes her
my friend, too.
It seems like I have
to keep coming to you
for help over and over
again today, huh?
Well, that's nothing new.
I am a little worried
about her, though.
You know what I mean...?
She still doesn't
remember anything at all
about the earthquake.
Yes. I think she's in
a mild state of shock.
That's what the doctor
at the hospital said,
and it seems to be true.
It was pretty scary, huh?
Yeah.
Well, at least the
fireworks show was awesome...
and nobody got badly hurt.
Now... you take excellent
care of Haru'ue, you hear me?
Yep, you just
leave it to me!
Oh... one more thing.
Thanks for all
your help tonight.
Oh... I didn't
know you were up.
What? Where am I?
Back in our dorm room...
How are you feeling?
Can I get you something
to drink or anything?
I'm sorry. I hope I wasn't
too much trouble tonight.
No trouble at all,
I promise you.
I'm strange.
I know that.
Now other people know, too,
and they don't
like me anymore.
That's not
going to happen!
For one thing...
you've got me
and I still like
you just fine.
Oh I can't believe
I almost forgot!
Saten brought you a get--well
treat to cheer you up.
Hold on just a second.
It's delicious.
Apparently, this came
from outside the city.
Saten says the ones we
have here are too bland,
and she wanted you
to have the best!
She's really nice.
Both you and Saten and
the others... all of you.
You've helped me so much.
I can't do anything.
All I'm good
at is waiting.
I hate being like this,
but it's true.
I wish I could change.
Don't give up.
You can change.
I would never have become
a Judgment officer
without all my
friends helping me.
We're on your side now.
We're going to help you.
So you'll be just fine.
Really? You think I can change?
Of course. In fact,
I guarantee it.
Now, eat your watermelon.
It'll make you feel better.
You're at Nature Park?
Together with Haru'ue?
That isn't fair!
Why didn't you invite me
to come along with you?
I didn't even know you were
off Judgment duty already.
I'm sorry.
I thought...
breathing fresh air...
would be nice,
for a change.
Have you overdosed
on fresh air?
You're way out of breath.
I'm fine, really.
A... okay.
Just dandy.
Aw.
I dropped by to
hang out with her,
and she's blowing me off.
Well, this isn't
exactly a place
where people
come to hang out.
I'm sorry about that.
I know...!
Why don't I go out
and get some snacks
for us to share?
A snack would be nice.
How about some ramen, some
fried rice, a seafood sampler
and let's see,
what else sounds good.?
You're hungry, huh?
Oh, and how about some
spring rolls, too.
You know, the kind
with shrimp in them.
Uh, you do know I'm not
paying for all this, right?
You know, I don't
feel good about this.
Yeah.
Same here...
but we have to do it
if we want to clear
Haru'ue's name, right...?
-There's no choice.
-Yeah, okay.
There she is.
It looks like her
ability is telepathy.
Psychological
responsiveness.
But she's still a Level 2.
Which basically means she
can't utilize it at all.
There, you see...!
Haru'ue doesn't have anything
to do with the poltergeisting...
I knew we were
getting ourselves
all worked up about nothing.
Wait, Sissy...
Look at this.
Ah! That breeze feels so good!
Have you noticed food tastes
better when you eat outside?
I guess that's why people
like going on picnics.
Um... about the other night.
I've been thinking a lot
about what you said.
How you told me I could
change if I wanted to
and how you'd be there
to help me if I tried.
Well, I've made
a decision.
I want... I want
to change, really.
That's a big
choice to make.
Yes, but I think
it's the right one.
And there's something
else I want to tell you.
You see, I...
I'm looking for a friend.
We were friends
for a long time...
always by each
other's side.
But then one day...
we got split up.
She made me promise that
someday, no matter what...
we'd meet up again.
All this time...
I've been waiting.
But I've made
up my mind.
Waiting isn't good
enough anymore.
I need to actually
start looking for her.
I'm here.... but who
knows where she is?
Okay, Haru'ue, we'll look
for your friend together.
And I'm sure
we'll find her.
Don't you worry!
Thank you so much.
What is it?
What are you doing?
I can't find you.
Where are you?
Why are you hurting?
Please, listen to me!
-What's going on?
-Where are you...?
-Haru'ue!
-Where are you?
What the...?!
Not again!
What's that beeping?
No, I'm telling you,
it's better than you think.
I'll get some for us.
A large--scale
poltergeist event!
Out in Nature Park?
That's where Uiharu
and Haru'ue are!
What's the casualty count?
72 people injured...
eighteen of them seriously...
No fatalities as of yet.
Continue with the
rescue operation.
Yes, ma'am.
It's true. You really
couldn't distinguish this
from the aftermath of
an actual earthquake.
Please just come with me.
It's okay.
You can let me go.
I'm a Judgment officer.
Please, just let me see
what I can do to help out.
It's you.
You were at the last one.
Miss Therestina?
You're here?
Uiharu!
Hi, guys.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Sorry you came
down here.
As you can see, I'm fine.
It's just a little
scrape, that's all.
I told them it
wasn't a big deal,
but they still insisted.
I'm glad you're okay.
You could have called...
We were worried about you!
You got caught in
poltergeisting events
two times in a row!
You and Haru'ue must be
the unluckiest people
in Academy City!
Now that I think about it,
where is Haru'ue?
She was evacuated
before me,
so she must be around
here somewhere.
It's okay, though,
she' not hurt...
She just passed out.
That's a relief.
It could've been a
lot worse than that.
Uiharu.
Think back to right
before it happened.
Do you remember Haru'ue
behaving strangely in any way?
You know, like what
happened to her
during the fireworks show.
Well, uh...
why are you asking?
According to my
investigation.
Haru'ue is a Level
Two telepath
with some irregularities
in her ability.
If you observed any
suspicious behavior,
like what happened before,
then you need to tell me...
Why?
Huh?
Why would you be
investigating Haru'ue?
Oh, well, you see...
No way.
You can't suspect Haru'ue
of being involved in this.
Well. Suspect is
a strong word.
How could you do this,
Shirai?
Haru'ue just transferred
to our District.
She's nervous, and she's
relying on us to help her...
and yet, you....
-You're horrible!
-Whoa, take it easy, Uiharu.
Listen, to her, Uiharu.
Kuroko didn't mean t...
It's certainly possible
that a telepath is
the one tampering
with the AIM diffusion fields.
We can't write it off.
Oh, I didn't
see you there.
It doesn't look like they
can take any more here.
Have the rest of the
injured sent to the hospital
in District Fifteen.
Right.
-What now?
-As I was saying.
A telepath could
indeed be responsible,
but they would have to be
a Level Four at least
and the number of people
who fit that description
is very small.
The chance of a Level Two
managing such a feat
is practically zero.
But I still think we
should look into this,
just to be on
the safe side.
Who is this
friend of yours?
A transfer student:
Erii Haru'ue
How could you?!
We're sending one victim
to the lab at headquarters.
-Have a car brought around.
-Please, no!
Just think of this as
proving her innocence.
It will be all right.
We have an excellent staff
of specialists at the lab.
She's in good hands.
And, you know, you shouldn't
shout in a hospital.
Here, have a drink.
No thanks,
I'm not thirsty.
Take it already.
Oh, hey...
is that watermelon tea?
That's perfect!
I'm dying of thirst over
here. Thanks a lot...!
Have one, Kuroko.
The exam is complete.
Is it...? Great...!
Where is she?
Please calm yourself.
It will still be a little
while before we get the results.
Now. Follow me.
Wow.
This doesn't really look much
like a laboratory, does it...?
It's not decorated
like one, anyway.
In this job you see a lot
of pain and suffering.
It's nice to remember
there are still pure,
beautiful things
in the world.
Huh...? You mean,
this stuff is all you?
Sure... I was the decorator.
All right. Shall we
have some introductions?
I'm Therestina, director of the
Multi Active Rescue Laboratory.
-The director?!
Do I have this right?
You're the commander of
the Multi Active Rescue team,
the director of
the entire lab.
I think that's it.
Or do you have more titles?
No, that's all.
And what about you?
Except for Shirai there,
I don't know any
of your names.
Tell me who you are.
Oh right, sorry.
My name's Mikoto Misaka.
From Tokiwadai Girls' school?
What an unexpected honor
to have the famous Railgun
here in my own lab.
No... really....
-And...
-Oh... I'm Ruiko Saten. Uh. Hi.
Are you at Tokiwadai, too?
No, I'm at Sakugawa.
If you're friends with
somebody like Misaka,
you must be quite an
esper in your own right.
No... actually...
I'm not.
Well, no matter...
Nice to meet you.
Oh... it's a pleasure
to meet you, too.
-And you are?
-Kazari Uiharu
officer with Judgment
Branch One--Seven--Seven.
I see...
So you and Shirai are...
Please! Haru'ue's not the
person you're looking for.
She's not some
kind of criminal!
Let's try something.
Tell me, what's
your favorite color?
I like all
colors, really...
If I have to pick,
I guess yellow.
Yellow, is it?
Well... we shall see.
What are you
doing, exactly?
There.
I'd say that's a good sign.
Huh?
Excuse me!
You would dare
to assault me?
You do know that I am
Mitsuko Kongo of Tokiwadai?
There's no assault.
Please, just listen...
As we've been
trying to explain,
cases of poltergeisting among
Level Fours are quite rare,
so further examination...
And as I've explained,
no exam is necessary.
There is absolutely
nothing wrong with me...
Ecaterina is waiting, so...
That's Shirai.
Shirai, Misaka,
can you hear me?
Quick, hold her down!
-Wait, what are you...
-Is something the matter?
No... it's nothing.
That's Haru'ue!
-Results in?
-Yes.
Let's see here.
Well? What is it?
You can relax now.
She isn't the person
we're looking for.
You were right about her.
She is a Level
Two telepath.
What's more,
she's only a receiver
and unable to send out
any messages herself.
But what about the note in
her record in the database
saying she exhibited
"anomalistic ability
above her level under
specific wavelengths?"
Be quiet!
Let it go!
Our examination
was quite thorough.
We found that she is limited
to a select number of partners.
She can pick up on those people
regardless of the distance
or any obstacles
in the way,
but she can't
hear anybody else.
Whatever the case.
It simply isn't possible for
her to tamper with AIM fields.
You see? Told you.
I was only doing my job.
So... If it's not her,
then who is the one
behind the poltergeisting?
Hi, Haru'ue.
Oh... Uiharu...
I guess I passed out again.
It's okay.
Everything's okay.
You don't have anything
to worry about now!
Here.
This pendant is important
to you, isn't it?
Yes... it's a memento
of a good friend.
You mean the
one you told me
you were looking
for earlier?
Yes, that's right.
I can hear her.
Like her voice?
That sounds like
telepathy to me.
It's only once in a while.
But when I do hear it.
I get lost in it somehow.
So that's what
those attacks are.
Is there a photograph
inside the pendant?
Yes.
See. Her name's Banri Edasaki.
It's that girl!
I've seen her before.
You know who Banri is?
Well, I...
There's something else.
I'm like her.
I'm a Child Error, too.
[Music]
So, Haru'ue is a Child Error.
Kuroko and Uiharu aren't
exactly on the best of terms.
I guess it's up to me to--
Wait! You again?!