You understand nothing!
I would do anything
to save them...
anything in the
entire world!
The whole city can
hate and revile me.
I don't care! I'm not going
to let anything stop me now!
Hey... what's wrong?
Oh, gosh...
what's that?
A fetus...?
[Music]
It's no use.
Every single camera
has gone dead.
My phone's not going
through, either.
Kuroko!
I can't just leave
Sissy alone out there!
How can you help her
with all these injuries?
Well, I....
You need to have more
faith in Misaka...
I'm sure she
can handle it.
A fetus...?
Is this the
"Metamorphose" skill?
I've heard about it.
I guess it's real.
This is bad...
It's getting bigger.
Hurry, Misaka!
Why are you here, Uiharu?!
Uiharu! You okay?
Yes... I'm fine.
You're lucky.
You shouldn't have
come down here!
Yeah... I'm sorry.
-But, I...
-Just stay there.
I'm not sure what
this thing is,
but if it wants a fight,
it can have one.
It's not after me.
What, then? Is it just
on a random rampage?
Look at it.
It's almost like it's
in pain or something.
-What's happening?
-The patients...!
They all suddenly
started going berserk.
We don't know why!
Have they regained
consciousness?
No... They were in the same
comatose state as usual.
-And then, this.
-All at the same time?
As if on cue...
They're all exhibiting
the same symptoms...
They haven't regained
conscious--ness;
it's more like they're
all experiencing
the same horrible dream.
Good grief!
What the hell is going on?
Hey, what is that thing?
A monster?
Some new kind
of bio--weapon?
We'll have to do what we
can with the men we have left.
Use of live ammo
is authorized...
Fire!
Look...!
I think...
it's getting bigger!
How incredible.
Who would've thought
something like that
could ever be created...?
I can just imagine
the recognition
I'll get from academia.
The network is utterly out
of my hands at this point.
That's it...
I no longer have any hope of
bringing back all those children
I helped to destroy...
They're lost forever.
Please! You can't give up now!
Is that an AIM
diffusion field?
It's most likely a
collection of them...
Yes, that's it...
Although I think it
would be more appropriate
to call it an AIM burst.
The AIM diffusion fields
of ten thousand people...
all bundled up together
within the Level Upper network.
They acted as the catalyst
to bring to life a monster
of latent consciousness.
Simply stated...
That thing up there
is a collection of ten
thousand children's thoughts.
Academy City...
all my dreams were going
to come true here...
I was going to be
a powerful esper.
But now...
My dreams have
become a nightmare.
It doesn't matter
how hard I try...
In this city,
if you have no talent,
you have no power.
So I'm stuck with my miserable,
ordinary life...
A life where every day
means being beaten down,
taken advantage of,
or simply ignored.
So what can I do?
I have no choice but to
get my hands on it...
I can't keep
living like this...
I'm so tired of
being powerless.
In a way...
I pity it.
What now? How do we
go about stopping it?
You're asking me
that question...?
It makes no difference
what I say...
You'll never trust me.
Then what about this...?
You're the one who took my
handcuffs off, aren't you?
That doesn't
mean anything...
You can't possibly trust
me just because of that.
That's not all.
I know you're sincere
about wanting to help bring
those children back...
I can hear it
in your voice.
I trust you.
I completely trust
you, Teacher.
You heard it, too?
There might be a way.
Think about it...
The AIM burst is a monster
created by the
Level Upper network...
If the network were
brought down somehow,
that might stop it.
The Level Upper
treatment program!
It might not work but it's
worth a shot at least.
I'll find a way to
handle that thing...
While I'm doing that,
You get that chip and
whatever's on it to Antiskill.
Right, let's do it!
Incredible...
There are still
people out there
who are willing to trust
without any reason to.
Captain!
No... No...!
No...! Stay away!
What were you just
standing there for?
That monster
could've killed you!
Uh... who are you?
A civilian
shouldn't be here!
It's too dangerous!
Geez...
Everybody just has to
call me a civilian.
It's starting to get old.
Whatever, just get away
from here right now!
You're the one who
should get going...
That thing won't
come this way
unless you provoke it
with more shooting.
Even so...
We can't just stand down
and do nothing either.
Do you know what
that is over there?
An experimental
nuclear reactor.
What?!
Hey, what's
that girl doing?
That's her!
The girl Kiyama
held hostage.
She sure is taking
her time getting away.
She's not.
Uiharu's not being held
against her will anymore,
and she's not
getting away.
I need to ask a favor.
From now on, you're
going to be facing me.
Geez...!
You're not going to make
this easy, are you?
No!
Thank goodness!
It's not broken.
I have to hurry...
Or it will be too
late for everyone.
I can do this...
I'm a member of Judgment.
For them.
And for Saten!
You okay?
Honestly!
You kids these days do
the craziest things.
Do you have the
treatment program?
Yes, it's safe.
We'll cover you...
Hurry!
Damn! Another one.
Didn't you hear
what I told you?
I said, you're
going to face me.
I'm your biggest
problem now.
So stop just standing there,
looking all creepy....
Go on, make a move!
Come after me, already!
By broadcasting the vaccine file
throughout Academy City...
you will bring down the
Level Upper network.
If the flower--haired
girl can manage that...
It should succeed in
bringing the runaway
AIM burst under control...
However...
It's starting to feel like
this could go on forever...
Sheesh!
What do you want with a
nuclear power facility anyway?
This is straight out
of a monster movie!
Oh, yeah?...
a collection of ten thousand
children's thoughts...
Oh, no!
Yes, that's right.
We're out of time.
Take the file I'm sending
and broadcast it by all means
possible throughout the city!
All right.
The transfer is complete!
I'll take responsibility...
Just play it right now!
What is that?
Doctor...! Look
at the patients!
Whatever I have to do,
I absolutely cannot allow it
to come any closer than this.
Music?
What is that?
Crap!
It won't matter how
many times I hit it
if it just keeps
regenerating.
It's not growing back.
That music must be the
treatment program...!
You did it, Uiharu!
Sorry about this...
but it's game
over for you now!
That was a closer
fight than I like.
Don't relax.
This isn't over yet!
Hey...! What do you
think you're doing here?
No way!
The network may
have been disrupted,
but remember, that's a mass of
ten thousand people's thoughts,
created by AIM
diffusion fields.
You can't think about it
like an ordinary creature.
This isn't what
we bargained for.
What am I supposed
to do, huh?
The nucleus!
There has to be a nucleus
where the fields have become
embedded somewhere inside.
That's the key...!
Find a way to destroy it.
Is that it?
Was that Saten?
Are Level Zeroes
permanently defective?
That's what they think.
I can't stand it.
It's hopeless...
As a Level Zero...
What's happening?
You probably...
wouldn't understand......
how miserable
every day is for us.
You come here with
so many expectations,
and then... nothing.
Stand back now...
Where you are,
you might get hit.
What do I care...?
I'm responsible for
creating that creature...
Maybe you don't care.
But what about the
students you taught?
Once we save them,
don't you think it's your face
they're gonna want to see?
I'll help you
save the children...
but I won't
help you die...
You shouldn't
give up so easily.
Got it?
I don't want you tangled
up in that thing.
I'm the one who's going
to tangle with it...
Right about now!
Incredible...
Is that the same kind
of induction field
I was using before...?
With power like hers...
maybe this will work.
The lightning isn't
hitting it directly.
But the heat from the electrical
impedance she's forcing on it
is blasting its body away.
When she was fighting
me earlier...
that wasn't her
full power at all.
Forgive me...
Anyone......
would want to be......
an esper...
I should have realized
so much sooner.
What's the use anymore?
I'll always be nothing.
There's no point.
I know how hard
you were trying.
I was so tired of not
having any power...
And finally, it
didn't matter anymore
what lengths I had
to go to to get it.
I understand.
But this doesn't
have to be it.
You can keep trying.
Don't stay here and let
yourself be defeated.
You are not defective.
There's nothing
wrong with you.
So... don't give up!
So that's it...
That's a Level 5.
It... worked.
Inspection of
experimental reactor core
and surrounding
area is complete.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Roger.
Do an additional sweep
to make sure no one was
injured in the area.
Wait... uh...
What now...?
What do we do?
About the children, I mean.
I have no intention
of giving up.
I'll just have
to try again.
It doesn't matter whether
I'm in a laboratory
or a prison cell.
They can lock me up but they
can't stop me from planning.
However...
I'm still not going to be
choosy about my methods...
If you don't like the
plan I come up with,
you'll have to come
and stop me again.
Good grief.
She's never gonna
learn, is she?
-Sissy! Sissy! Sissy!!
-Oh... Kuroko...
I was worried about you!
My heart was aching
the whole time...!
And look at you:
hair messed up,
scrapes and bruises
all over your skin!
And I'm guessing you don't
have the strength left
to shock, either...
I think I'll take
this time to examine
every inch of your
body for injuries
and rub the soreness
from your limbs.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I received a message from
the hospital with good news.
It looks like all the people
who used the Level Upper
are beginning to
regain consciousness.
And we have you to
thank for that...
Good job.
Now then, Sissy, let's
pick up where we left off.
What are you doing?
Knock it off!
I swear, if you don't
stop this second...
There you are!
Oh, hey, Uiharu!
Don't "oh, hey" me!
I've been looking
everywhere for you!
Why aren't you
in your room...?
Are you sure you should
be out of bed so soon?
There could still
be something wrong.
You were in a coma!
I just took a long
nap, that's all...
I'm totally back
to normal now.
Including not having
any kind of ability.
What is it?
I'm sorry...
for getting hung up
on stupid stuff...
and for keeping
secrets from you...
and for putting you
through all of this.
You don't have to...
But I am...
I came so close...
So close to losing something
far more important to me
than some stupid ability.
Oh, yeah...
I almost forgot.
I'm back!!
What did you do that for?
Get back to your
bed right now!
I was just thanking you
for taking care of me!
Though, I think
you should know,
even your panties
are covered in mud.
That settles it. Things are
officially back to normal.
How can you say that?
After everything
I've done,
you're insulting
my underwear?!
Is something
bothering you?
Huh...? No, it's nothing.
"Can we really
blame the people
who used the Level Upper for
making the choice they did?"
"Maybe we're responsible
for all of this;
we espers, who didn't realize
how much pain they were in,
how hard it must
be to live here
and not have an ability."
That's what you
were thinking,
or something
along those lines.
Am I right?
Don't mimic me...
It's creepy.
That kind of compassion
is just like you, Sissy.
And while we're on the
topic of compassion,
there's one other thing
I wish you would give
some thought to...
and that is...
My feelings...
I deserve some
love too, don't I?
I should thank
you, Kuroko...
Your unrelentingly,
unapologetically
perverted nature
is giving me some
of my strength back.
-I'm serious here, Saten!
-You are gonna get it...!
Careful, Misaka!
Oh, dear! Shirai,
are you all right?
Some things never
change, huh?
[Music]
After all we just
went through,
isn't this kind of a
cheap thing to do?
What are you talking about?
A swimsuit episode
is perfect.
Here, tell me which
one you like better...
-Sissy, look!
-I don't want to!