All I could do before
was lift a paper cup.
This is the most
amazing thing ever!
Ruiko...?
It's happening...
I'm doing something.
How could you drop
me like that, Akemi?!
Hey, easy!
C'mon, just let her go!
-That was so uncool!
-Ouch, you're hurting me!
It's not much...
nothing like what Shirai
and Misaka can do...
but it's something...
finally...
After all this time,
I'm an esper now, too.
I can't believe it...!
It's too good to be
true...! but it is!
[Music]
There. All done.
Being able to level up
just by simply
listening to a song...
How can something like
that even be possible?
I don't fully
understand it, either,
but that's what our
informant told me.
Well I'm not sure
I believe it.
But what if I
did listen to it
and became an even stronger
esper than you are...?
That would
certainly open up
a whole world of
possibilities to me.
And what would these
possibilities be?
Perhaps you should go
ahead and give it a try
so we can find out.
Ah I'm kidding...!
Just kidding...
I would never do
that, I promise!
Hear that...?
Sounds like your
phone is ringing.
Yes...
Yes... I understand....
It seems we've got another
situation on our hands...
Contact Dr. Kiyama,
will you, please?
Yeah, I'm on it.
Yes. The item has
already arrived.
Can it really be
possible for someone
to raise their ability level
by listening to a song?
That is the question, huh?
With a Testament maybe.
Using a Testament?
Do you have such a device?
Oh...
Yes...
yes...
You don't say...
Okay, thanks
for everything.
I wonder if we could be
barking up the wrong tree
with this music idea.
Oh, Saten, I'm so
glad you answered...
The phone you have dialed is
either out of signal range
or has been turned off...
Please try your
call again later.
Pretty impressive power,
dontcha think?
The Level Upper
strikes again, huh?
You wanna mess with me...?
Go ahead and try it.
See what happens.
This must be pretty
embarrassing for you.
Bring it.
I'll show you my power!
Man... I wish these creeps
would give up already!
Okay, this is gonna
sting a bit...
It seems like you're getting
bruised up every day.
There are so many people
using Level Uppers now,
it doesn't seem like I
have much of a choice.
I wish there was some way
we could figure out
how far this craze was
spreading, y'know?
Wishing won't do any good.
This is going
to take work.
We need a plan...
There are three
things I think
we should be doing about this.
First, we get the
item off the street,
and then we help those
who've fallen into a coma.
And then...
We arrest whoever
is responsible.
We'll find out who
created this thing
and made it available.
And somehow or another,
we'll learn what their true
motive was for doing it.
Well... let's get you
taken care of first.
Are you sure you
wouldn't rather have
Misaka wrap you up, though?
I would just as soon not have
anybody see me like this,
much less my Sissy.
I promise Shirai, nobody
wants to see you like this.
Hey, guys! I just
wanted to see
if there was anything
I could do-
Oh... Hey, Sissy...
great to see you.
So, are you guys making
any progress with the case?
Hard to say...
We have uncovered some
new information...
From what
Dr. Kiyama tells us,
there's a certain
device called a Testament,
which is able to electrically
input a large quantity of data
directly into the brain.
However, it operates using
all of the five human senses.
Taste, touch, hearing,
smell and sight:
all are at work
with this thing.
But we know the Level Upper
is a music file,
so the only sense that
it uses is hearing.
We searched the rooms
of all the users
who are now in
vegetative states,
but we didn't come up
with any relevant data
other than the song.
Okay let's look at
this hypothetically...
Do you think
there's any way
the song could have an
effect on all five senses,
instead of just hearing?
I don't really understand.
Remember that
conversation we had
when we were eating
the shaved ice?
Let me see...
About brain freezes?
No that's not what I meant.
It's synesthesia!
Synes--what?
Something we were talking
about the other day...
It's what occurs when a
single thing stimulates
more than one
of the senses.
You stimulate one sense
with a particular method,
and others react too,
even though those senses
weren't the original targets.
So in this case,
do you mean
by stimulating the
senses using sound,
you could get
the same effect
you would get by
using a Testament?
Yes, it is a possibility.
I had overlooked
that until now.
Would you mind pursuing that
avenue of investigation?
Yeah... and in this case,
I should even be able
to get permission
to use Tree Diagram.
Tree Diagram, really?!..
Academy City's
greatest supercomputer
should speed things up!
I'll be in touch once
I have the results.
Would you mind if I headed
over there right now...?
I'd love the chance to
see Tree Diagram at work.
It must be amazing.
Sure... come on over.
Nice, huh...? I can
do this after only
five days of practicing.
Have you seen what
I've been doing?
It's all amazing.
Maybe I should at least
tell Uiharu about all this.
Knowing her, though, she'll
be mad at me for doing it.
-Akemi!
-Akemi...! What happened?
-Akemi, wake up!
-Are you okay?
-Akemi!
Finally, you answered...
I've been worried
about you....
You seemed really
distant at school,
and I haven't been able
to get you on the phone.
all of a sudden.
-What?
-Akemi.
She just collapsed
all of a sudden.
I didn't know that
using the Level Upper
could make anything
like that happen....
She just fell down
out of nowhere.
It's like something
out of a bad dream.
I can't believe this...
I just-I had no idea.
Okay...
You need to calm down...
Go slow. Start
from the beginning.
Well, the thing is, I got
my hands on a Level Upper.
You said anyone found
in possession of one
would be in trouble...
But I couldn't bring
myself to get rid of it.
And then Akemi
and the others said
they really wanted one...
No... the truth is...
I... I was too afraid
to use it by myself.
Never mind.
Where are you now?
Do you think whatever this
is will happen to me, too?
And if it does,...
will I ever wake up?
Or will I be
unconscious forever?
I couldn't take it...
I was so tired of
not having any power.
And finally, it
didn't matter anymore
what lengths I had
to go to to get it.
Mama...
Huh...?
What did you just say?
Maybe Level Zeroes like me
are permanently defective.
No, don't talk like that.
I ignored the rules
and went looking for power
of my own, anyway...
Maybe I'm being
punished for that.
I got involved in
something dangerous...
and it hurt my friends...
I... I'm awful!
It'll be okay!
If you fall asleep,
I'll wake you up...
It's not gonna be forever,
I promise you!
You, and Akemi,
and everybody else
who's gotten sick.
We'll make you all
better in no time!
I know it!
So you just sit back and
leave everything to me,
understand?!
Saten, you just need
to hang in there,
and things will get better
before you know it!
Uiharu...
Being a Level Zero doesn't
make you defective.
Even without abilities,
you're so full of
life and energy,
it's a challenge to keep
up with you every day.
No amount of power could
make you more incredible
than you already
are to me.
You're my best
friend in the world!
So stop it...
just stop it!
Stop saying such
horrible things...
because they aren't true!
You're asking me to put all
my trust in you on this one?
No, I'm not saying
it's just me!
There's Misaka and Shirai
and lots of other people
working on it, too.
Yes...
of course there are...
Thanks a lot...
You're a good friend.
Sorry for causing
so much trouble.
I'll let you handle
it from here, okay?
Saten... no!
So, Saten used
the Level Upper?
Yes.
Uiharu wanted to make
sure Saten was here
and as stable as they could
make her right now.
Then she took the data
and hurried to Dr. Kiyama.
Oh.
Do you have a second?
What did you want to
talk about out here?
Saten had a good
luck charm...
Do you remember it?
Oh, wait... the thing she always
had dangling from her bag?
That's the one...
She said she got it as a
gift from her mother...
right before she
came to Academy City.
She told you that?
It sounds very personal.
Yeah...
I get the feeling there
were a lot of things
she wanted to tell me.
But I just froze up.
They can call me a
Level 5 all they want...
but I'm not any good when
it comes to this stuff.
Aw, that's not true.
It's the kind of
person I am...
someone places a
hurdle in front of me,
and I can't rest until
I've jumped over it.
That's how I felt about
reaching Level 5...
It never seemed like
anything particularly great.
But...
I guess there are some
hurdles that you can't cross.
I'd never thought how
difficult it must be
to be in that situation.
"Does your Level really
matter that much?"...
Come on.
How inconsiderate can I be?
Will you please let me help
you out with this one case...?
I feel like it's
something I owe to Saten.
I guess I can do that.
That's awesome...
Thanks Kuroko.
I... I should be thanking you.
Do you have a moment?
A real Gekota!
Calm down, Sissy,
he's just a normal doctor.
What we're looking at
are the brainwave patterns
of the Level Upper victims.
Brainwaves vary from
person to person,
so the waveforms should
all be quite different
across the board.
However, I noticed something
surprising in this case.
Each of the
Level Upper victims
has a common
brainwave pattern.
What does that
mean, exactly?
It could point to an
outside influence...
Perhaps somebody else
is forcing their brains
into these
particular patterns,
and thus controlling the
function of their bodies.
So someone controlling
the Level Upper
is tampering with their brains
to put them all into a coma?
Why would somebody
want to do that?
I'm just a humble doctor
reporting my findings to you...
Determining the
motive is your job.
I see.
That girl we met
the other day.
I feel so responsible.
You can't blame yourself
for what happened to her...
Sit here and calm down...
I'm going to put
on some coffee.
This is no time to
be calm and relaxed.
The results of the analysis
haven't come through yet...
If she wakes up to find
you've collapsed...
that's not going to do
either one of you
any good will it?
It will be okay...
I'm sure everything is going
to work out in the end.
If this really does match
a specific person's
brainwave pattern...
All we have to do
is have Uiharu
run a search through
the databank, and...
Right, Uiharu isn't
here to do that.
Yeah, that's a problem.
Goodness, what's all the moaning
and groaning about in here?
Well, since you asked...
If that's the case,
the first step we'll need to
take is to access the databank
to get the information.
What if the data
isn't in the databank?
It will be
there somewhere.
Data is stored on any adult
who has been to the hospital
or taken a vocational
aptitude test,
along with all
the students
undergoing ability
development.
Okay... but this is all
still really confusing...
How could using
the Level Upper
reprogram somebody's
brain waves?
And moreover,
how would doing that
raise somebody's
ability level...?
So much of this
seems impossible.
It's like a computer.
Not even one of those
will increase in performance
that dramatically
just because you're running
different software on it.
Unless it's connected
to a network, anyway.
So a computer's
performance increases
when connected to a network?
Well, individually,
there's no major improvement...
But you can connect a lot
of different computers
in a parallel network...
then their computing
power does increase.
That's it...
Whoever's behind this
is constructing a
network of brains!
And they're doing it
with the Level Upper!
Well, it is a possibility.
But how does it work?
What's connecting all of
their brainwaves together?
If I had to make
a guess, then...
maybe an AIM
diffusion field...?
All espers emit a
force around themselves
without even
being aware of it.
If those were to
be connected....
But you said espers do
that unconsciously...
Besides, if we're comparing
humans to computers,
wouldn't we all run different
operating systems...?
How would it be possible
to link up together, then?
Computers in a network
also have different
operating systems;
they even use
different languages.
But networks can be created
by putting certain
protocols in place.
So in this case,
you're saying
that a particular
person's brainwave pattern
is serving as the protocol
for the whole network?
It's all speculation
at this point.
Okay... and if a
number of brains
were connected like that...
they would be able to do an
enormous amount of computing.
So one person might have
only a weak ability,
but by plugging
into the network,
the throughput of that
ability would increase,
making the person
significantly stronger.
Add to that the collective
thought patterns of espers
who have the same talent,
and you'd be able to manage that
ability much more efficiently.
It would be an incredible
boost in power.
So my hypothesis is that
all the brain activity of the
coma patients is being used
to power this network.
Hey, here we go!
The brain patterns' agreement
rate is ninety--nine percent.
This, too...
and this.
These are all papers
on synesthesia...
but why?
How impolite of you.
Looking at somebody's
research papers
without asking permission.
Can... can it be true?
Registrant name...
Harumi Kiyama?!
Uiharu!
What do you mean?
What about her?
She said earlier that she was on
her way to Dr. iyama's office!
What's she doing?
Uiharu!
I'm not getting
through to her.
Contact Antiskill
and have them take the
doctor into custody...
but be sure to warn them.
There might be a hostage.
Right!
You know something...?
I've been wondering about
this for a while now...
What's with all the
flowers in your hair...?
Does it have something to do
with your ability as an esper?
I don't see why I should
answer your questions.
But I have some for you...
I want you to tell me
about the Level Upper.
Why have you done
all of this...?
What will happen to the
people who are sick?
You are full of questions...
And yet you refuse to
answer the single question
I asked of you.
What do you get out of randomly
increasing someone's ability...?
You raise their hopes, and
then you put them in a coma?
Saten's a kind,
loving person.
She doesn't deserve
something like this.
I have no interest at all
in other people's abilities.
My ultimate objective is
much greater than that.
I'm coming along, too.
Although I don't normally like
getting civilians involved...
having someone with
your power around
could be beneficial.
Hold on, Sissy!
Don't forget Uiharu's
a member of Judgment.
She can handle herself
if she needs to.
Probably...
if she's lucky...
It isn't that unlikely...
Besides, Antiskill is
getting involved, too.
I doubt a scrawny
scientist like her
will be able to do
much against them.
The lives of thousands of
comatose espers are in her hands
as we speak.
Plus...
I've just got a bad
feeling about this-
You're right...
This could be bad...
Which is why a
Judgment officer...
Are you in good enough
shape to go into action?
You mean you knew...
about all my injuries?
Yeah, of course I did.
You may be strong, but I'm
still the older one here.
It's been a rough week...
so you can turn
to your Sissy.
Thank you, Sissy.
[Music]
I had a great time today...
And I think I'll finish by
undressing for the preview...
-Next time...
-Keep your clothes on!
And get ready, 'cause
I'm taking you down!