Kirito:
I'M NINETY‐NINE PERCENT SURE
THE DEATH GUN STORY'S A HOAX,
PROBABLY SOMEONE TROLLING.
YOU CAN'T KILL SOMEONE
IN THE REAL WORLD
FROM THE VIRTUAL ANYMORE.
I KNOW THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT THERE'S STILL
THAT ONE PERCENT CHANCE
IT COULD BE TRUE.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
LINK START!
IT'S A LOT DIFFERENT
THAN A. L. O.
GO FIGURE. KILLING PEOPLE'S
THE POINT IN HERE.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
HMM?
(GASPS)
HOLY CRAP!
I WISH I LOOKED
A LITTLE MORE SOLDIERISH.
Player: HOLY BAZONGERS!
THAT'S THE F‐1300 MODEL,
ISN'T IT?!
THAT AVATAR'S SO RARE,
I'VE ONLY HEARD ABOUT THEM
TILL NOW.
I WANT IT.
I'LL GIVE YOU TWO MEGA‐CREDITS
FOR YOUR ACCOUNT.
COME ON, LADY.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
Kirito: L‐LADY?
(GASPS)
UM, HATE TO BREAK IT YOU, GUY,
BUT I'M A GUY, TOO.
Player: HOLY CRAP!
THEN THAT MEANS
YOU GOT THE M‐9000 MODEL!
I'LL GIVE YOU FOUR,
NO, FIVE FOR IT.
SELL IT TO ME.
COME ON. SELL IT TO ME.
Kirito: SORRY, BUT THIS
ISN'T A DEFAULT AVATAR.
IT'S A CONVERTED ONE.
I CAN'T EXCHANGE IT FOR CASH.
Player: AWW, THAT SUCKS.
Kirito: YEAH, WELL, LATER.
Player: HEY, IF YOU
EVER CHANGE YOUR MIND,
GIVE ME THE FIRST BID.
Kirito: (GROANS)
IF I WANT TO GET
DEATH GUN'S ATTENTION,
I HAVE TO MAKE A NAME
FOR MYSELF FIRST.
Player 2: (WHISTLES)
Player 3: LOOKING FOR
SOME ACTION? 'CAUSE HERE IT IS.
WHAT? ARE YOU TOO GOOD FOR ME?
Kirito: I'M TOTALLY LOST.
SOME SHORTCUT
THIS TURNED OUT TO BE.
UH, EXCUSE ME.
CAN YOU TELL ME WHERE...
UH‐OH.
SHE THINKS I'M HITTING ON HER.
Sinon: YEAH? WHAT?
Kirito: UH...
Sinon: YOUR FIRST TIME
IN THE GAME, HUH?
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
I, UM...
OH, MY GOD.
SHE THINKS I'M A GIRL, TOO.
Sinon: WHERE DO YOU WANNA GO?
Kirito: UH...
I, UH...
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANING)
YES, IT'S MY FIRST TIME.
I'M LOOKING FOR A PLACE
TO BUY A CHEAP GUN.
OH, AND I ALSO NEED TO FIND OUT
WHERE THE GOVERNOR'S OFFICE IS.
(GIGGLES)
Sinon: OH. SURE.
I CAN SHOW YOU.
Kirito: IT'S NOT COOL,
BUT I'LL LET HER KEEP THINKING
I'M A GIRL FOR A WHILE.
Sinon: BY THE WAY,
WHY DO YOU WANT TO GO
TO THE GOVERNOR'S OFFICE?
Kirito: UH, I WANTED
TO SIGN MYSELF UP
FOR AN EVENT
CALLED BULLET OF BULLETS.
Sinon: B. O. B.?
OKAY, BUT YOU JUST STARTED
PLAYING TODAY, RIGHT?
Kirito: YES.
Sinon: YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
YOUR STATS MAY NOT BE
HIGH ENOUGH FOR THAT.
Kirito: OH.
WELL, I CONVERTED,
SO ALL MY SKILLS HAVE BEEN
TRANSFERRED FROM ANOTHER GAME.
Sinon: IF YOU SAY SO.
SO, ANYWAY, YOU PICKED
A HECK OF A GAME TO PLAY.
IT'S ALL GRIMY
AND STINKS OF OIL.
Kirito: MM, WELL, I'VE ONLY
PLAYED FANTASY GAMES UP TO NOW.
THEY'RE FUN, BUT I THOUGHT
I'D TRY A CYBER‐GAME FOR ONCE.
I WAS ALSO INTERESTED IN SEEING
WHAT GUN BATTLES WERE LIKE.
Sinon: REALLY?
IT TAKES GUTS TO WANT
TO START WITH B. O. B.
RIGHT OFF THE BAT LIKE THAT.
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: LET'S HOOK YOU UP
WITH A GUN THEN.
I KNOW THIS GREAT MARKET.
IT'S DOWN HERE.
Kirito: OKAY.
WOW. THIS PLACE LOOKS
LIKE IT HAS EVERYTHING.
Sinon: YEAH, WELL,
THE TWO TYPES OF WEAPONS
THAT ARE MOSTLY USED IN GGO
ARE OPTICAL GUNS
AND LIVE‐AMMO GUNS.
Kirito: HUH.
Sinon:
AN OPTICAL GUN'S LIGHTER
AND MORE ACCURATE,
BUT IT HAS ITS DRAWBACKS.
IF YOUR OPPONENT
EQUIPS THEIR DEFENSE SHIELD,
IT ONLY DOES HALF THE DAMAGE.
FOR A ONE‐ON‐ONE TOURNEY
LIKE B. O. B.,
A LIVE‐AMMO GUN'S THE BEST BET.
Kirito: OH. OKAY.
Sinon: ALL RIGHT,
LET'S START WITH YOUR STATS,
HIGHEST ONE FIRST.
Kirito: UM, I GUESS
MY STRENGTH IS THE HIGHEST,
AND SPEED AFTER THAT.
Sinon: YOU'RE
AN STR‐AGI TYPE, HUH?
OKAY, YOU'VE GOT TWO CHOICES
FOR YOUR MAIN WEAPON,
EITHER A HEAVY ASSAULT RIFLE
OR A LARGE‐CALIBER MACHINE GUN.
WHICHEVER ONE YOU CHOOSE,
YOU'RE ALSO GONNA NEED A HANDGUN
FOR A BACKUP WEAPON.
OH, WAIT A SEC.
YOU SAID YOU JUST
CONVERTED OVER, DIDN'T YOU?
DO YOU HAVE ANY CREDITS?
Kirito: YEAH, I SHOULD.
LET'S SEE.
IT SAYS I HAVE
A THOUSAND CREDITS.
Sinon: EVERYBODY GETS THAT
WHEN THEY START.
Kirito: OH. (LAUGHS)
Sinon: HMM.
IF THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE,
THE MOST YOU CAN AFFORD'S
GONNA BE A SMALL RAY GUN.
AND FOR A LIVE‐AMMO GUN,
A THOUSAND WON'T EVEN
GET YOU A USED REVOLVER.
LISTEN, IF YOU WANT,
I COULD LOAN YOU THE MONEY
TO BUY A GUN.
Kirito:
THAT'S REALLY SWEET OF YOU,
BUT I COULDN'T. UH, I KNOW.
DOES THIS GAME
HAVE ANYTHING IN IT
WHERE A NEW PLAYER LIKE ME
COULD GO EARN SOME MONEY?
Sinon: WELL,
I DON'T RECOMMEND THEM,
BUT THERE ARE CASINOS
AND GAMBLING GAMES,
LIKE THAT ONE.
Gunslinger:
HEY, CHICKEN, COME ON.
Kirito: HOW DO YOU PLAY?
Sinon: YOU ENTER
THROUGH THAT GATE
AND GO DOWN THE ALLEY,
DODGING THE NPC's BULLETS.
THE IDEA IS TO GET
AS CLOSE AS YOU CAN TO HIM
WITHOUT GETTING SHOT.
IF YOU CAN TOUCH HIM,
YOU WIN ALL THE CASH
EVERYONE'S SUNK INTO IT
SINCE THE LAST TIME
IT WAS BEAT.
Kirito: ALL OF IT?!
Sinon: THREE HUNDRED THOU
AND CHANGE.
Kirito: NOW, THAT IS
A HECK OF A LOT OF MONEY.
Sinon: WELL,
NO ONE'S BEATEN IT.
ONCE YOU GET EIGHT METERS
AWAY FROM THE GUNSLINGER,
HE SWITCHES TO THIS
WICKED‐FAST QUICK‐DRAW MODE.
BY THE TIME YOU SEE
THE BULLET LINES, IT'S TOO LATE.
Kirito: THE BULLET LINES?
Sinon: LOOK.
ANOTHER SUCKER'S
STEPPING UP
TO ADD TO THE JACKPOT.
Player 4:
TODAY'S THE DAY, MAN.
Player 5: YEAH, YOU GOT THIS.
Player 6: HERE GOES NOTHIN'.
Gunslinger:
I'M GONNA BLAST YOU
FROM HERE TO THE MOON,
YA VARMINT.
Players: (LAUGHING)
Player 7: HURRY UP,
AND DIE ALREADY.
Player 6: WATCH ME CLEAR
THIS BEEYOTCH IN NOTHING FLAT.
Player 4: JACKPOT'S YOURS.
Player 6: YEAH, YOU KNOW IT.
Kirito: WHY'S HE DOING THAT?
Spectators: (CHEERING)
Kirito: WAS THAT
THE BULLET LINE?
Sinon: YEP.
IT'S A DEFENSIVE SYSTEM ASSIST.
WE ALL HAVE IT.
EXCEPT FOR
A SNIPER'S FIRST SHOT,
BULLET PREDICTION LINES
ALWAYS SHOW UP
IN THE TARGET'S FIELD OF VISION.
Gunslinger: I'LL KILL YA.
Player 6: WHATEVER.
(LAUGHS)
Player 4: RUN, MAN!
Player 5: YOU SO GOT THIS!
Gunslinger: YOU LOSER.
GAME OVER, HOSS.
Player 8: WELL, THAT SUCKED.
Player 9: THAT GUY
DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE.
Sinon: SEE?
THAT ALLEY IS SO NARROW,
YOU CAN'T MOVE
TOO FAR TO EITHER SIDE,
AND YOU'RE FORCED TO CHARGE
THE GUNSLINGER STRAIGHT ON.
THAT'S ABOUT AS FAR
AS ANYONE'S GOTTEN.
Kirito: AH, I GET IT.
IF I WAIT TO SEE
THE BULLET LINES,
IT'LL BE TOO LATE.
Sinon: UH, HEY,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
Player 6: TEN CREDS SAYS
THE NEWBIE GETS IT
OUT OF THE GATE.
Player 9: WHOA.
THAT'S THE CUTEST TARGET
I EVER SEEN.
Player 8: LET'S STICK AROUND
AND WATCH HER GET PWNED.
Gunslinger: I'LL KILL YA.
YOU LOSER.
Sinon: YOU'RE KIDDING.
Player 6: SHE PASSED
THE TEN‐METER MARK.
Player 4:
THAT IS ONE FAST KID.
Gunslinger: DIE, YOU VARMINT.
I'LL BLAST YOU TO HELL!
Kirito: LOOKS LIKE
SOMEONE'S OUT OF BULLETS.
Gunslinger: NO!
HEY, CHICKEN, COME ON.
Player 9:
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
Player 8: WHO IS THAT KID?
Sinon: OH, MY GOD.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
REFLEXES LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, AT THE END,
YOU DODGED HIS LASERS
FROM ABOUT TWO METERS AWAY.
AT THAT RANGE, THE TIME BETWEEN
YOU SEEING THE BULLET LINES
AND THE SHOTS FIRED‐‐
WELL, THAT'S IT.
THERE SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
ANY TIME BETWEEN 'EM.
Kirito: OH. UM...
REALLY?
WELL, SINCE IT'S A GAME
OF DODGING BULLETS,
I JUST PREDICTED
THE BULLET LINES.
YOU KNOW,
PREDICT THE PREDICTIONS.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Sinon: YOU‐‐YOU PREDICTED
THE PREDICTIONS?!
Gunslinger: HUH?
(KIRITO GROANS)
I'M CONFUSED ABOUT THE SPECS
FOR THIS ASSAULT RIFLE.
I MEAN,
THIS THING'S GINORMOUS,
SO WHY'S THE CALIBER
OF THE BULLETS IT FIRES
SMALLER THAN
A SUBMACHINE GUN'S?
Sinon: I'M CONFUSED
ABOUT HOW SOMEONE LIKE YOU
CAN DODGE BULLETS LIKE A GHOST
AND NOT KNOW THAT.
YOU CONVERTED
FROM ANOTHER GAME.
WHAT'D YOU PLAY
BEFORE THIS ONE?
Kirito: NOTHING SPECIAL.
JUST ONE OF THOSE TYPICAL
FANTASY GAMES, IS ALL.
Sinon: HMM.
YEAH, SO YOU SAID.
WELL, DURING THE B. O. B. PRELIMS,
I'LL GET AN IDEA
OF WHAT YOU CAN REALLY DO.
Kirito: (LAUGHS)
Sinon: AS FOR
THE ASSAULT RIFLE,
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY
IT USES A SMALL CALIBER?
Kirito: SURE.
Sinon: IT ALL GOES BACK
TO THE M16 FROM THE U. S.
THEY DESIGNED IT FOR PRECISION
AND PENETRATIVE POWER,
BUT USING A FAST,
SMALL‐CALIBER ROUND.
YOU DON'T NEED TO KNOW
THAT STUFF, THOUGH.
NOW THAT YOU'VE GOT
THREE HUNDRED K,
YOU CAN BUY PRETTY MUCH
WHATEVER GUN YOU WANT.
IT ALL COMES DOWN
TO WHAT YOU WANT
AND WHAT YOU THINK'LL
WORK BEST FOR YOU.
Kirito:
WHAT DOES WORK FOR ME?
HMM.
HEY, WHAT ARE THESE?
Sinon: OH, THOSE ARE
PHOTON SWORDS.
Kirito: PHOTON.
Sinon: IT'S A BEAM OF LIGHT
THAT'S A WAVE
AND A PARTICLE.
PHOTON SWORD'S
THE OFFICIAL NAME,
BUT PEOPLE CALL 'EM
LASER BLADES, BEAM SABERS,
AND SOMETHING ELSE
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
Kirito: OH, COOL!
YOU CAN USE A SWORD HERE?
Sinon: YEAH, IF YOU WANT,
BUT NOBODY REALLY USES THEM.
Kirito: WHY DON'T THEY?
Sinon: WELL, I MEAN,
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T USE IT
UNLESS YOU'RE CLOSE
TO YOUR TARGET,
AND IF YOU'RE CRAZY ENOUGH
TO GET THAT CLOSE,
YOU'LL GET SHOT
FULL OF HOLES.
Kirito:
SO BASICALLY IT'S GOOD
AS LONG AS YOU
GET CLOSE ENOUGH.
Sinon: YEAH, I GUESS,
BUT EVEN WITH
YOUR SKILL AT DODGING,
IF THERE'S A FULL‐AUTO GUN
FIRING AT YO‐‐
UGH.
Robot: WELCOME, PLAYER.
Kirito: THANK YOU.
Robot: THANK YOU
FOR YOUR PURCHASE.
HAVE A NICE DAY.
Sinon: OH, WELL.
I GUESS
WHEN IT COMES TO COMBAT,
EVERYONE'S GOT
THEIR OWN STYLE.
Kirito: THE WAY I SEE IT,
IF THIS PLACE SELLS SOMETHING,
IT MUST BE OKAY FOR BATTLE,
EVEN THIS.
Both: WHOA.
Sinon: HUH.
SHE LOOKS LIKE SHE KNOWS
WHAT SHE'S DOING.
WOW.
THOSE ARE
YOUR FANTASY GAME SKILLS?
NOT BAD.
Kirito: I KNOW
A COUPLE OF MOVES.
THIS SURE IS LIGHT.
Sinon: HUH?
WELL, LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE DEAD SET
ON THAT FOR YOUR MAIN WEAPON,
BUT YOU SHOULD HAVE
A SUBMACHINE GUN
OR A HANDGUN
IN YOUR INVENTORY, TOO.
IT'LL DISTRACT YOUR ENEMY
SO YOU CAN GET CLOSER.
Kirito: OH, OKAY.
Sinon: HOW MUCH
DO YOU HAVE LEFT?
Kirito: ABOUT A HUNDRED‐FIFTY K.
Sinon: WHOA. THOSE
PHOTON THINGIES ARE EXPENSIVE.
YOU GOT
A HUNDRED AND FIFTY K, HUH?
YOU STILL NEED TO GET
PROTECTIVE GEAR,
SOME KIND OF WEAPON,
AND THE AMMO FOR IT.
WHAT'S CHEAP, BUT GOOD?
Kirito: I'LL TRUST
YOUR JUDGMENT WITH ALL THAT.
Sinon: FOR B. O. B.,
A LIVE‐AMMO WEAPON'S
YOUR BEST BET.
IF I WERE YOU, I'D GO FOR
ACCURACY OVER STOPPING POWER.
HMM.
OH. YOU'LL SPEND MOST
OF YOUR CREDITS ON IT,
BUT THIS ONE'S GOOD,
THE FN FIVE SEVEN.
Kirito: WHAT'S FIVE SEVEN?
Sinon: THE BULLET CALIBER,
5.7 MILLIMETERS.
THEY'RE SMALLER THAN
THE NINE‐MILL
PARABELLUM BULLETS,
BUT THEY STILL PACK A PUNCH.
THEY'RE SIMILAR IN SHAPE
TO RIFLE BULLETS,
SO THEY'VE GOT THE EDGE
IN BOTH PRECISION
AND STOPPING POWER.
Kirito: HUH.
Sinon: HEY, ARE YOU
EVEN LISTENING?
Kirito: HUH? OH, YEAH.
I GUESS I'LL BUY
THAT ONE THEN.
IS THAT IT,
OR DO I NEED ANYTHING ELSE?
Sinon: YEAH, YOU DO.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED A HOLSTER,
SOME EXTRA MAGS,
SOME PROTECTIVE GEAR.
AND YOU SHOULD ALSO GET YOURSELF
A DEFENSE FIELD AND RANGE TIME.
Kirito: WHAT'S THAT?
Sinon: YOU NEVER FIRED
A GUN BEFORE, HAVE YOU?
Kirito: UH‐UH, NEVER.
Sinon: LET'S CHANGE THAT.
Kirito: (GROANS)
Sinon: IF YOU BUY A GUN
FROM THE SHOP,
YOU CAN TEST IT HERE.
KNOW HOW TO HOLD IT?
Kirito: I GUESS.
IT'S LIGHTER THAN I THOUGHT.
Sinon: THAT'S 'CAUSE
THAT MODEL'S
MADE OF REINFORCED PLASTIC.
THE RECOIL
ISN'T TOO BAD ON IT.
STILL, YOU SHOULD GRIP IT
WITH BOTH HANDS.
AND KEEP YOUR LEFT EYE OPEN.
Kirito: OH, OKAY.
(HEART BEATING)
Sinon: SO RIGHT NOW,
YOU SHOULD BE SEEING
A GREEN CIRCLE
IN YOUR FIELD OF VISION.
Kirito: IS IT SUPPOSED TO BE
SHRINKING AND EXPANDING
LIKE THAT?
Sinon: YEP.
IT'S CALLED
THE BULLET CIRCLE,
YOUR OFFENSIVE ASSIST SYSTEM.
YOUR BULLETS'LL HIT
THE TARGET AT RANDOM
INSIDE THE CIRCLE.
Kirito: HOW DO I BOOST
MY ACCURACY?
Sinon: I GUESS THE EASIEST WAY
IS TO GET CLOSER TO YOUR TARGET.
Kirito: WHAT ELSE?
Sinon: TRY TO STAY CALM.
THE FASTER YOUR HEART BEATS,
THE MORE THE CIRCLE EXPANDS.
Kirito: THIS IS
HARDER THAN I THOUGHT.
NO WAY.
I MISSED?
Sinon: WHAT'D YOU EXPECT?
IT'S YOUR FIRST TIME.
Kirito: THANK YOU FOR GOING
OUT OF YOUR WAY FOR ME.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
Sinon: MM‐MMM.
I WAS HAPPY TO HELP.
THERE AREN'T
MANY GIRL PLAYERS HERE.
I WASN'T DOING ANYTHING,
SO IT WAS A GOOD WAY
TO KILL SOME TIME
BEFORE THE PRELIMS.
Kirito: WAIT. YOU'RE GONNA
COMPETE IN B. O. B., TOO?
Sinon: UH‐HUH. I WAS
ON MY WAY TO SIGN UP BEFORE...
OH, MY GOD.
THEY'RE CLOSING SOON.
Kirito: REALLY?
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S MY FAULT WE'RE LATE.
Sinon: NO, IT'S MINE FOR NOT
KEEPING TRACK OF THE TIME.
WHATEVER. LET'S HURRY.
Kirito: WE'RE NEVER
GONNA MAKE IT.
CAN'T WE JUST TELEPORT
OVER THERE?
Sinon: I WISH. THAT ONLY
HAPPENS WHEN YOU RESPAWN
AT A REVIVAL POINT
AFTER YOU DIE.
AND WE CAN'T SUICIDE OURSELVES
TO GET THERE EITHER,
'CAUSE IN TOWN,
OUR H. P. NEVER GOES DOWN.
THE GOVERNOR'S OFFICE IS
AT LEAST THREE KILOMETERS AWAY.
IT'S GONNA TAKE US
FIVE MINUTES TO SIGN UP,
SO WE HAVE TO GET THERE
IN THREE.
DON'T CLOSE.
DON'T CLOSE
TILL WE GET THERE.
Kirito: THAT'S IT.
HERE WE GO.
Sinon: (SCREAMS)
Kirito: BETTER HANG ON!
Sinon: WAIT A SEC.
THESE ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
RIDICULOUSLY HARD TO DRIVE.
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE
WHO CAN HANDLE 'EM,
SO HOW COME YOU CAN?
Kirito: OH, WELL,
I USED TO PLAY
A LOT OF RACING GAMES
BACK IN THE DAY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
Sinon: (LAUGHS)
YEAH, I'M FINE.
THIS IS GREAT.
GO ON. PUNCH IT.
THE FASTER, THE BETTER.
Kirito: OKAY.