Nori: HEY, GUYS!
Asuna: WE MIGHT NOT
TAKE DOWN THIS BOSS,
BUT THE NEXT ONE,
I PROMISE THAT ONE'S OURS!
Players: (GASP)
Kirito: SORRY, GUYS.
STAND DOWN.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING PAST ME.
Asuna: KIRITO!
Player: YOU SURE
YOU WANNA DO THIS, BUDDY?
IT'S A BAD IDEA.
I DOUBT EVEN YOU CAN TAKE ON
A HORDE THIS BIG SOLO.
Kirito: YEAH, MAYBE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT FOR SURE.
Player: IT'S YOUR FUNERAL.
OKAY, PEOPLE,
YOU HEARD THE MAN.
MAGES, LET HIM HAVE IT.
Mages: ECK, BULBAH, EIN, SREAL.
Asuna: WATCH OUT, KIRITO!
‐ (GEAR RATTLES)
‐ (GASPS)
‐ Mage: SMUGAH, STECKLE...
‐ Mage 2: ISKALDOL, SKEAL...
‐ ORBINUL!
‐ ALEOO!
Kirito: HEH.
Yuuki: NO WAY.
Talken: HE CUT THEIR SPELLS.
Tecchi: BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
Player: EH, I DIDN'T KNOW
HE COULD DO STUFF LIKE THAT.
Player 2: NOW YOU KNOW.
Player 1: HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
Kirito: EASY.
COMPARED TO A BULLET
FROM A HIGH‐POWERED RIFLE,
KNOCKING DOWN
HIGH‐SPEED SPELLS IS NOTHING.
Player 1: AH, CRAP.
B‐BATTLE FORMATION
ON THE DOUBLE!
Players: (GASPING)
‐ Mage 1: ECK, BULBAH, SREAL...
‐ Mage 2: ECK, SKEATOH, SREAL...
Kirito: I CAN ONLY HOLD 'EM
FOR A COUPLE!
HEAD FOR THE BOSS ROOM! HURRY!
Players: (GASP)
Player 1: OH, YEAH?
HOLD YOUR GROUND!
THERE'S ONLY ONE OF HIM!
Klein: NOT EVEN!
‐ I'M HERE, TOO!
‐ Player 3: (GRUNTS)
Klein: YOU JUST
CAN'T SEE ME YET!
Kirito: YOU'RE LATE!
WHAT THE HELL TOOK YOU SO LONG?
Klein: SORRY, MAN!
TOOK A WRONG TURN.
Asuna: KLEIN'S HERE, TOO?
(GASPS)
THANK YOU, YUI.
YOU, TOO, KLEIN.
AND, KIRITO, I LOVE YOU.
MY FRIENDS WILL TAKE CARE
OF THOSE PLAYERS,
BUT IF WE WANT TO GET
INTO THE BOSS ROOM TODAY,
WE'LL HAVE TO GET THROUGH
THE ONES BLOCKING IT
OURSELVES.
Yuuki: GOTCHA!
Players: (GRUNT)
Asuna: READY?
Yuuki: YUP!
Jun: (YELLS)
Tecchi: (GRUNTS)
Player 4: (YELPS)
Nori: (YELLS)
Yuuki: (GIGGLES)
(LAUGHS)
(GASPS)
HEY! NO FAIR!
Asuna: THINK YOU CAN HEAL THEM
ON YOUR OWN FOR A BIT?
Siune: SURE. I SHOULD HAVE
ENOUGH MANA FOR THAT.
Asuna: GREAT. THEN I'M GONNA
TAKE CARE OF THOSE ENEMY MAGES.
YUUKI! WATCH OUT!
Yuuki: HUH?
WHOA! WHAAH!
Players: (YELLING)
Mage 3: IT'S THE BERSERK HEALER!
Asuna: (YELLS)
Sleeping Knights: (PANTING)
Asuna: ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
THE HARD PART'S NEXT.
COME ON. LET'S GET THAT BOSS.
Sleeping Knights: RIGHT!
Jun and Tecchi: (GRUNT)
Asuna: (GASPS)
YEAH. WE WILL BEAT HIM.
OKAY, DRINK YOUR POTIONS, GUYS.
MAX OUT YOUR H. P. AND M. P.
STICK TO THE PLAN,
AND WE'LL HAVE A SHOT.
WE KNOW AT THE START,
ITS ATTACK PATTERNS ARE SIMPLE.
STAY CALM, AND AVOID THEM.
HMM?
Yuuki: ASUNA...
THOSE GUYS,
THOSE FRIENDS OF YOURS,
ARE THEY HERE JUST TO HELP US?
Asuna: YES.
THEY KNOW IT'S IMPORTANT TO YOU,
SO LET'S PULL THIS RAID OFF
AND MAKE IT WORTH THEIR EFFORT.
Yuuki: YEAH, BUT...
I MEAN,
WE CAN'T LET YOU DO ALL THIS
AND NOT GIVE YOU
ANYTHING IN RETURN.
Asuna: BUT YOU HAVE.
YOU TAUGHT ME SOMETHING
I'M ALWAYS GOING TO REMEMBER.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO FIGHT
TO GET YOUR POINT ACROSS, RIGHT?
‐ Sleeping Knights: (CHUCKLING)
‐ Siune: MM‐HMM.
Asuna: WELL, THIS IS
OUR LAST CHANCE AT THIS.
TIME'S RUNNING OUT.
IT WON'T BE LONG
BEFORE THAT GUILD REGROUPS
AND COMES CHARGING
THROUGH THAT DOOR.
LET'S DO OUR BEST TO WIN
SO WE CAN FLASH THEM
A VICTORY SIGN WHEN THEY DO.
HEY, YUUKI,
WHEN THIS BATTLE IS OVER,
I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
ALL ABOUT YOURSELF.
I WANT TO KNOW ABOUT
ALL THE WORLDS YOU'VE BEEN TO
AND ALL THE ADVENTURES
YOU'VE HAD.
Boss: (ROARING)
‐ Yuuki: (GRUNTS)
‐ Asuna: (GASPS)
Yuuki: HERE COMES
THE BOSS, GUYS!
LET'S MESS HIM UP!
Sleeping Knights: RIGHT!
Boss: (ROARING)
‐ Asuna: SEH‐AH, FILLA!
‐ Siune: SEH‐AH, FILLA!
Yuuki: (LAUGHS)
(YELLS)
Siune: ONLY THREE LEFT.
Asuna: YOU GUYS,
WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
DON'T LET UP ON HIM!
Yuuki: RIGHT!
Talken: (YELPS)
Boss: (GROANS)
Tecchi: THAT BOSS SURE KNOWS
HOW TO DEFEND ITSELF.
YOU THINK THAT'S A RANDOM MOVE,
USING HIS ARMS TO BLOCK?
Asuna: SIUNE, I HAVE AN IDEA,
AND I NEED YOUR HELP.
CAN YOU TAKE OVER HEALING
FOR THIRTY SECONDS?
Siune: YES,
THAT SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
I HAVE ENOUGH RESERVES
TO COVER EVERYONE.
Asuna: ECK, SKEAT,
FIO‐RIL, ISKALDOL, ALE!
Boss: (GROANS)
Asuna: I KNEW IT.
THAT WASN'T RANDOM.
IT'S PROTECTING A CRITICAL
WEAK SPOT WITH THAT MOVE.
YOU SEE THAT JEWEL ON ITS CHEST?
THAT'S WHERE WE NEED
TO FOCUS OUR ATTACK.
Siune: SO WE
JUST SHATTER THAT JEWEL,
AND WE CAN DEFEAT IT?
Asuna: AT THE VERY LEAST,
WE'LL PUT A DENT IN ITS H. P.
THING IS,
IT'S TOO HIGH UP TO REACH,
AND WE CAN'T FLY
IN THIS DUNGEON.
Siune: THEN WE'LL
JUST USE OUR SWORD SKILLS
AND KEEP AN EYE OUT
FOR COUNTERMOVES.
Asuna: SOUNDS GOOD.
I'LL GO UP FRONT
AND TELL THEM THE PLAN.
HEAL THEM
FOR A LITTLE LONGER, OKAY?
Siune: DON'T WORRY. I'M ON IT!
Asuna: YUUKI!
Yuuki: ASUNA! WHAT'S GOING ON?
Asuna: GUESS WHAT.
I FOUND A WEAK SPOT ON THE BOSS.
YOU SEE THAT JEWEL ON ITS CHEST,
BELOW THE NECKS?
IF YOU HIT THAT,
YOU'LL DO SOME MAJOR DAMAGE.
Yuuki: YOU SURE? (GASPS)
Jun: HERE YA GO!
Yuuki: IT'S HIGH.
I COULDN'T REACH IT,
EVEN IF I JUMPED.
Asuna: YOU COULD IF YOU HAD
THE RIGHT SPRINGBOARD, THOUGH.
Yuuki: HUH? (LAUGHS)
Asuna: TECCHI!
WHEN HE SWINGS
THAT HAMMER AGAIN,
TAKE A KNEE!
Tecchi: MM.
Asuna: IT'S OUR CHANCE TO WIN.
GOOD LUCK, YUUKI!
Yuuki: LEAVE IT TO ME, SIS!
Asuna: UH, "SIS"?
Yuuki: (YELLS)
Boss: (ROARING)
(FANFARE PLAYING)
Asuna: WE DID IT.
Yuuki: YOU SEE THAT?!
(LAUGHS)
WE DID IT! WE DID IT! WE DID IT!
WE BEAT HIM, ASUNA!
Asuna: THAT, WE DID.
(CHUCKLES)
I'M SO TIRED.
Jun: WE DID IT.
Tecchi: YEAH, BUT I'M WIPED.
Both: (GIGGLE)
‐ (DOORS GRINDING)
‐ (GASP)
Players: (GASPING)
Player 1: OH, MY GOD.
Both: (LAUGH)
Players: (GASPING)
Sleeping Knights: (CHUCKLE)
Player 1: (GASPS) YOU‐‐
YOU‐‐YOU‐‐
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
‐ Sleeping Knights: YAY!
‐ Tecchi: ALL RIGHT!
Asuna: GREAT JOB, YOU GUYS!
I'M KIND OF SAD IT'S OVER.
Siune: OH, IT'S NOT OVER YET.
Asuna: HUH?
Siune: THERE'S
ONE LAST THING TO DO.
Asuna: UM...
Siune: YOU KNOW, A PARTY?
Asuna: OH!
(LAUGHS) OF COURSE!
(LAUGHS)
LET'S HAVE A BIG ONE.
WE'LL PULL OUT ALL THE STOPS.
Jun: SWEET! WE GOT ENOUGH NOW
TO PARTY IN STYLE, RIGHT?
Tecchi: MM‐HMM.
Jun: WHERE ARE WE GONNA HAVE IT?
HEY, WE SHOULD GO
TO SOME BIG CITY
AND BUY OUT A RESTAURANT
FOR THE NIGHT.
‐ Asuna: UM...
‐ Talken: WHAT?
Asuna: ACTUALLY,
IF YOU GUYS WANT TO,
WE COULD HAVE IT
AT MY PLACE IN‐GAME.
IT'S SMALL, BUT COZY.
Yuuki: REALLY?!
OH.
Asuna: Y‐YUUKI,
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
Yuuki: UM...
Siune: PLEASE FORGIVE US, ASUNA.
WE REALLY APPRECIATE
YOUR OFFER TO HOST THE PARTY.
IT'S JUST THAT...
OH, NEVER MIND. IT'S NOTHING.
WE'D BE HONORED
TO HAVE OUR VICTORY PARTY
AT YOUR HOME, ASUNA.
Nori: THAT SETTLES IT.
GUYS, WE'RE HEADING OVER
TO THE LOMBARD CENTRAL MARKET.
WE GOT OURSELVES
SOME SHOPPING TO DO.
Tecchi: HELL TO THE YES!
Jun: LET'S GET SOME OF THAT ALE!
Yuuki: WOW.
YOUR PLACE IS SO COOL, ASUNA.
WAIT. THERE'S ALREADY
FOOD AND DRINKS OUT.
Talken: WHOA.
Tecchi: NOW THAT'S
WHAT I'M TALKING 'BOUT!
‐ MAN, LOOK AT THAT THING.
‐ Siune: SMELLS AMAZING.
Jun: AH, IT SMELLS SO GOOD.
Tecchi: I'M GONNA DIG IN, OKAY?
Nori: PUT THOSE
OVER THERE, YEAH?
Asuna: (CHUCKLES)
Nori: YOU'RE NOT SCARED
OF A LITTLE ALKIE‐HOL, ARE YA?
Talken: NO!
I JUST WANNA PACE MYSELF.
Yuuki: OKAY, SO THE WORST M.M.O.
I EVER PLAYED WAS...
THIS ONE FROM THE U.S.
CALLED INSEC‐SITE.
Siune: (SHUDDERS)
THAT ONE'S BAD.
Asuna: REALLY?
WHY DIDN'T YOU LIKE IT?
Yuuki: BUGS EVERYWHERE!
IF IT WERE JUST THE MONSTERS,
NO PROBLEM,
BUT YOU GOTTA PLAY AS A BUG!
I HAD TO PLAY AS A BIPEDAL ANT,
SO I GUESS
I DIDN'T HAVE IT TOO BAD,
BUT YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN HER.
Siune: (GASPS) NO!
PLEASE DON'T SAY ANYTHING!
Yuuki: SHE WAS
A GIANT CATERPILLAR!
SPITTIN' SILK LIKE WHOO!
‐ (LAUGHS)
‐ Siune: (GROANS)
Asuna: (LAUGHS) THAT'S AWESOME.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU GOT TO TRAVEL
TO SOME REALLY COOL PLACES
TOGETHER.
Yuuki: HOW 'BOUT YOU?
I MEAN, YOU COME OFF
LIKE YOU'VE BEEN PLAYING
V. R. M. M. O. s FOREVER.
Asuna: DO I?
WELL, I PLAY THIS ONE A LOT.
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW MANY HOURS IT TOOK
TO GET THE MONEY
TO BUY THIS CABIN.
Yuuki: WORTH IT.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU SAID
THIS PLACE WAS COZY,
YOU WEREN'T KIDDING.
IT'S GOT THIS REALLY COOL
OLD‐TIMEY VIBE.
Siune: YES, IT DOES.
IT'S SO PEACEFUL,
I COULD SIT HERE ALL DAY.
(GASPS)
Asuna: W‐WHAT'S WRONG, SIUNE?
I'M SO SORRY,
BUT I JUST REMEMBERED.
WHEN WE ASKED YOU TO HELP,
WE SAID WE'D GIVE YOU WHATEVER
THE BOSS DROPPED IN RETURN.
IT WAS MONEY, THOUGH,
AND WE SPENT A LOT OF IT ON FOOD
AND DRINK FOR OUR PARTY.
Talken: WHAT HAVE WE DONE?
‐ Sleeping Knights: (GROAN)
‐ Talken: AW, MAN.
Yuuki: CRAP! NOW WE DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO GIVE YOU.
Asuna: NO, IT'S OKAY.
HOW ABOUT A FAVOR INSTEAD?
Yuuki: FAVOR?
Asuna: UH‐HUH.
HONESTLY, I'M A LITTLE SAD
THE QUEST IS OVER.
I WANT TO GET TO KNOW YOU
BETTER, YUUKI.
THERE ARE SO MANY THINGS
I WANT TO ASK YOU.
Yuuki: ASUNA,
SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA FIGHT
TO GET YOUR POINT ACROSS.
Asuna: YUUKI...
WOULD YOU LET ME JOIN
THE SLEEPING KNIGHTS?
Sleeping Knights: (GASP)
Yuuki: ASUNA,
I WISH YOU COULD, BUT...
IT'S LIKE THIS IS
A TEMPORARY THING FOR US,
AND, LIKE, COME SPRING,
WE'LL BE SPLITTING UP,
AND AFTER THAT,
I DOUBT ANY OF US'LL
BE DIVING MUCH ANY MORE.
Asuna: I KNOW,
BUT CAN I JOIN UNTIL THEN?
I WANT US TO BE FRIENDS.
I WANT TO BE FRIENDS
WITH ALL OF YOU.
THERE'S STILL ENOUGH TIME
FOR THAT, ISN'T THERE?
Yuuki: I‐I'M SORRY, ASUNA.
YOU CAN'T. SORRY.
Asuna: NOT AT ALL. IT'S FINE.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE PUT YOU
ON THE SPOT LIKE THAT, YUUKI.
I'M SORRY.
Siune: UM, ASUNA,
I DON'T‐‐YOU SEE, WE‐‐
Asuna: NO, REALLY,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE.
SORRY I WAS SO PUSHY.
ANYWAY, COME ON.
LET'S GO CHECK IT OUT.
Siune: WHAT?
Asuna: THE REASON
WE BEAT THE BOSS, REMEMBER?
YOU KNOW, THE MONUMENT
IN THE BLACK IRON PALACE.
I'M SURE
IT'S BEEN UPDATED BY NOW.
Jun: YEAH, GUYS! LET'S GO! OH.
KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD DO?
WE SHOULD TAKE
OUR PICTURE WITH IT.
‐ Talken: GOOD IDEA.
‐ Tecchi: BEST ONE YET.
‐ Nori: OH, MY GOSH...
‐ Tecchi: COME ON, GUYS.
‐ LET'S GO!
‐ Asuna: HEY, LET'S GO.
Tecchi: ANYONE WANT
TO SEE IT AS BAD AS I DO?
Jun: THEY'LL REMEMBER OUR NAMES
TILL THE END OF TIME.
‐ Tecchi: COME ON.
‐ Jun: ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
I CAN'T WAIT.
Jun: THERE IT IS!
‐ Nori: HEY! WAIT FOR ME!
‐ Yuuki: HOLD UP!
Sleeping Knights: (LAUGH)
Yuuki: LOOK. UP THERE.
THERE WE ARE.
WE GOT OUR NAMES ON IT.
Jun: HEY, GUYS,
LET'S TAKE THAT PICTURE!
Asuna: COME ON, YUUKI.
BIG SMILE.
Yuuki: (CHUCKLES)
Jun: (CHUCKLES)
(CAMERA BEEPING)
Both: (LAUGH)
Asuna: THERE IT IS. YOU DID IT.
Yuuki: YEAH,
I FINALLY DID, HUH, SIS?
Asuna: (CHUCKLES)
THERE YOU GO AGAIN, YUUKI.
Yuuki: WHAT?
YOU CALLED ME SIS JUST NOW,
THAT'S WHAT.
AND IN THE BOSS ROOM, TOO.
Yuuki: (GASPS)
Asuna: IT'S FINE.
IT MAKES ME HAPPY.
(GASPS)
Yuuki: (CRYING)
Asuna: W‐WHAT'S WRONG?
Yuuki: ASUNA...
I‐I...
Asuna: YUUKI.