Leafa: HIS FAST‐ACTING MIND
IS ONE REASON.
Asuna: HUH.
(GASPS)
Silica: (SIGHS)
Asuna: WAKE UP.
IF YOU START NAPPING NOW,
IT'S GONNA BE HARD
TO GET TO SLEEP TONIGHT.
THERE'S THREE DAYS
OF WINTER BREAK LEFT,
AND YOUR HOMEWORK
WON'T FINISH ITSELF.
SINON FINISHED HERS BEFORE
HEADING BACK HOME TO VISIT.
‐ Silica: (YAWNS)
‐ Asuna: JUST SAYING.
Silica: I'M SO SLEEPY.
Asuna: POOR THING.
IT'S PROBABLY 'CAUSE
THE ROOM'S TOO WARM.
YOU WANT ME
TO TURN DOWN THE HEAT?
Leafa: (LAUGHS)
IT'S NOT THE HEAT.
IT'S THE MASTERS
OF THE SLEEP SKILL OVER THERE.
Asuna: HUH?
OH. WELL, THAT FIGURES.
HE'S BEEN WORKING HARD
ON HIS PROJECT
EVER SINCE HE GOT BACK
FROM "G. G. O."
Lisbeth: YOU MEAN
THAT GIZMO FOR YUI
HE DEMOED
THE OTHER DAY AT AGIL'S?
Leafa: OH, THE MECHA‐PHONICS?
Lisbeth and Asuna:
NO, IT'S CALLED MECHATRONICS.
Leafa: UH, YEAH, THAT.
ANYWAY, HE'S NAPPING
LIKE THERE'S NO TOMORROW.
LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S MAKING ME FEEL SLEEPY.
Lisbeth: (YAWNS)
Both: (LAUGH)
Asuna: HMM.
(COUNTRY‐WESTERN MUSIC PLAYING)
Agil: HERE YOU GO.
YO, GUYS, SERIOUSLY,
Y'ALL DON'T HAVE TO COME HERE
EVERY TIME YOU'RE ON A DATE.
THERE'S CLASSIER PLACES IN TOWN
YOU COULD GO TO.
Kirito: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THIS PLACE IS PLENTY CLASSY,
COMPARED TO YOUR SHOP
IN ALGADE, ANYWAY.
Agil: (GROWLS)
Asuna: OH, DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
I LIKED IT.
Kirito: THAT PLACE
WAS A RIP‐OFF.
HALF THAT JUNK
WAS PAPIER‐MACHE.
Asuna: HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
HE WAS LETTING YOU
STAY THERE FOR FREE.
Agil: THANK YOU.
Kirito: THAT'S GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
Asuna: OH, WHATEVER.
Kirito: OKAY, SPILL IT.
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
Agil: NOTHING.
JUST SEEING YOU LIKE THIS.
Y'ALL DON'T LOOK ANYTHING LIKE
THE ASSAULT TEAM'S TOP PLAYERS.
Kirito:
RIGHT BACK AT YOU, BUDDY.
Asuna: HEH. WELL, ON THAT NOTE,
I BET YOU'VE PLAYED MMORPGs
FOR A LONG TIME, HUH?
Agil: TRUE THAT.
I PLAYED SO MUCH,
I MET THE MISSUS IN‐GAME.
SHE USED TO LIVE IN THE U. S.,
AND WE FELL FOR EACH OTHER HARD.
A YEAR LATER, SHE WAS HERE
RUNNING THE PLACE WITH ME.
Y'ALL NEVER KNOW
WHAT LIFE'S GOT PLANNED FOR YOU.
Asuna: AWW!
Kirito: IF KLEIN
HEARD THAT STORY,
HE'D POP A BLOOD VESSEL.
Agil: ANYWAY, WE GOT MARRIED.
NEXT BIG STEP
WAS GETTING OURSELVES
A PAIR OF NERVEGEAR RIGS.
BUT WHEN THE TIME CAME,
WE COULD ONLY PREORDER ONE.
HEH. I REMEMBER
WE PLAYED SOME GAME
TO SEE WHO'D GET
TO TRY IT FIRST.
I'M GLAD IT WAS ME WHO CRACKED
THE SEAL ON IT, NOT HER.
STILL FEEL THAT WAY.
THE ASSAULT TEAM
WAS THE ONLY TICKET OUT.
THAT'S WHY I JOINED UP WITH 'EM.
ALL I WANTED WAS TO GET BACK
TO THIS PLACE AND TO MY LADY.
Kirito: I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
I WANTED TO GET BACK
TO MY FAMILY, TOO.
IT'S WHAT KEPT ME
ALIVE IN THERE.
Agil: YOU AND THE ASSAULT TEAM,
BROTHER.
HELL, MAN, I BET
EVERY PLAYER IN AINCRAD
FELT THE SAME WAY
ABOUT GOING HOME AGAIN.
RIGHT, ASUNA?
AIN'T THAT WHAT MOTIVATED YOU?
Asuna: HMM. NO, NOT REALLY.
I‐I MEAN, IT'S COMPLICATED
BETWEEN ME AND MY FAMILY.
I GUESS THAT'S WHY THERE ARE
A COUPLE TIMES IN THERE
I ALMOST FORGOT
WHAT I WAS FIGHTING FOR.
SOMETIMES I FELT LIKE
I DIDN'T BELONG ANYWHERE.
REAL AND VIRTUAL
WERE BOTH DEAD ENDS.
BUT THEN I MET KIRITO.
HE GAVE ME SOMETHING
I COULD COME HOME TO,
A PLACE THAT FELT
MORE LIKE A HOME
THAN ANYTHING I EVER HAD
IN THE REAL WORLD.
I WAS HAPPY,
EVEN THOUGH I KNEW
ONCE "S. A. O." WAS CLEARED,
OUR CABIN WOULD BE GONE.
BUT I KNEW DEEP DOWN
THAT ONE DAY,
SOMEHOW I'D HAVE A HOME AGAIN
WITH KIRITO AND YUI.
THAT'S WHAT FINALLY GAVE ME
THE STRENGTH TO FIGHT
AND KEEP FIGHTING.
IT GAVE ME HOPE.
(GASPS)
(GIGGLES)
Agil: (CLEARS THROAT)
Both: (GASP)
Agil: SPEAKING OF AINCRAD,
KIDDIES.
THE MODS JUST POSTED SOME INFO
ON THE NEXT UPDATE.
IT'S MOSTLY TYPICAL STUFF.
THEY'RE GONNA BE ADDING
NEW WEAPONS AND SWORD SKILLS.
BUT THEY'RE ALSO
GONNA BE UNLOCKING
FLOORS 21 TO 30
IN NEW AINCRAD. BOOM.
Kirito: WAIT.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?!
Asuna: IF WE BEAT
THE BOSS ON FLOOR 21,
WE HAVE A CHANCE TO BUY
THAT LOG CABIN AGAIN.
Kirito: YEAH.
YEAH, BUT THERE'S BEEN A TON
OF LITTLE CHANGES
TO NEW AINCRAD LATELY.
IT'D SUCK TO GET OUR HOPES UP
JUST TO FIND
OUR CABIN'S NOT THERE.
Asuna: YEAH, IT WOULD.
BUT I KNOW IT'S THERE.
IT'LL BE WAITING FOR US
JUST LIKE HOW WE LEFT IT.
‐ Asuna: HEH.
‐ Agil: (SIGHS)
WELL, Y'ALL BETTER
GET A MOVE ON THEN.
UPDATE GOES LIVE CHRISTMAS EVE.
(WEAPONS CLASHING)
Monster: (ROARS)
Players: (GRUNTING)
Asuna: SA‐YAHH SHAHL
LINDOH‐ASHEENA
BART AIMEE ORGH‐SVERLD.
Agil: (YELLS)
Kirito: (YELLS)
Players: (YELLING)
(CHORUS SINGING)
Players: (MURMURING)
Players: (YELL)
Asuna: I'M GOING IN!
(GASPS)
Sinon: ASUNA.
KEEP GOING. I'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
Kirito: ASUNA, YOU AND ME!
Yui: WATCH OUT, DADDY!
IT'S ABOUT TO PUNCH!
Monster: (GROWLS)
Kirito: SWITCH OUT!
Asuna: (YELLS)
(CHORUS ENDS)
(FOOTSTEPS CLATTERING)
Silica: I BEAT YA!
Klein: WHOA.
ALL RIGHT!
WE MADE IT TO FLOOR 22!
Lisbeth: (GRUNTS)
HUH?
HEH.
HEY, ASUNA,
IF YOU'RE HANGING AROUND
'CAUSE OF THE TELEPORT GATE,
DON'T BOTHER.
WE CAN ACTIVATE IT.
‐ Leafa: MM‐HMM.
‐ Agil: HEH.
Asuna: (GASPS)
THANKS A LOT, YOU GUYS.
Both: (CHUCKLE)
Asuna: (GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
ARE YOU SEEING THIS?
‐ Kirito: MM‐HMM.
‐ Asuna: (LAUGHS)
(GIGGLES)
Both: (CHUCKLE)
Asuna: (SIGHS)
Yui: (GIGGLES)
Asuna: HERE WE GO. YOU READY?
(LAUGHS)
Asuna: (GASPING)
Yui: HEH.
OH.
Asuna: HEH.
I'M HOME.
Leafa: OH, MY GOD, SERIOUSLY?
HEY, ASUNA, WAKE UP!
Asuna: HUH?
Leafa: (SIGHS)
THAT GOES FOR YOU, TOO.
Lisbeth: HUH?
(SIGHS)
GOD, WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S LIKE HE'S DARING US
TO STAY AWAKE.
Asuna: (LAUGHS)
I'LL MAKE SOME MORE TEA,
AND IT'LL WAKE US RIGHT UP.
Silica: HEY, LOOK.
I GUESS IT STOPPED SNOWING
WHILE WE WERE SLEEPING.
Leafa: YEAH.
IT REALLY CAME DOWN.
Lisbeth: OH,
HAVE YOU HEARD THE NEWS?
Asuna: WHAT?
Lisbeth: YOU KNOW, ABOUT ZEKKEN?
DON'T TELL ME YOU HAVEN'T HEARD.
Asuna: ZEK‐KEN?
Asuna: ZEKKEN? IS THAT SOME KIND
OF RARE ITEM OR SOMETHING?
Lisbeth: ERRH! WRONG.
IT'S THE NAME OF A PLAYER.
ACTUALLY, IT'S NOT THEIR HANDLE.
IT'S MORE LIKE A NICKNAME.
ANYWAY, THIS PLAYER'S SO BADASS,
SOMEONE CALLED THEM ZEKKEN.
THE NAME CAUGHT ON,
AND THERE YOU GO.
IT MEANS "ABSOLUTE SWORD."
ULTIMATE SWORD'S BETTER, THOUGH.
EITHER WAY, THIS PLAYER'S TOUGH.
Asuna: REALLY?
SO, UH, WHEN DID YOU FIRST HEAR
ABOUT THIS ZEKKEN PERSON?
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS MAYBE THE FIRST TIME
WAS AROUND NEW YEAR'S
OR SOMETHING,
MAYBE A WEEK OR SO AGO.
OH, DUH. THAT EXPLAINS
WHY YOU'RE
SO OUT OF THE LOOP ABOUT IT.
YOU'VE BEEN
AT YOUR FAMILY'S COMPOUND
IN KYOTO THIS WHOLE TIME.
Asuna: (GROANS)
I WAS HAVING A GOOD TIME,
BUT YOU HAD TO BRING THAT UP.
Lisbeth: LISTEN TO THE RICH GIRL
REBELING AGAINST HER CUSHY LIFE.
SOUNDS LIKE A DRAG.
Asuna: A DRAG
IS EXACTLY WHAT IT WAS.
I HAD TO SIT ON MY KNEES
IN A KIMONO ALL DAY
GREETING PEOPLE.
I BROUGHT MY AMUSPHERE ALONG,
THINKING I COULD DIVE AT NIGHT
WHILE EVERYONE WAS ASLEEP,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE GUESTHOUSE I WAS IN
DIDN'T HAVE WI‐FI.
FUN, RIGHT?
IT WASN'T.
‐ (MUSIC PLAYING)
‐ (NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE )
Lisbeth: ASUNA.
ASUNA.
YOU EVEN LISTENING? HELLO.
Asuna: HUH? S‐SORRY.
I JUST REMEMBERED
SOMETHING LAME.
Lisbeth: I WONDER
WHAT THAT COULD BE.
WERE YOUR FOLKS TRYING
TO HOOK YOU UP WITH SOMEONE?
Asuna: N‐NO, NOT AT ALL!
FORGET I SAID ANYTHING.
Lisbeth: (LAUGHS)
OKAY, OKAY. JUST KIDDING.
Asuna: SO, ANYWAY,
IS THIS TOUGH NEW PLAYER
A PK‐er OR SOMETHING?
Lisbeth: MM‐MM.
JUST A DUELIST. THAT'S ALL.
Asuna: WERE THEY
IN ANY TOURNAMENTS?
Lisbeth: NOPE.
AS FAR AS I KNOW,
THIS PLAYER'S A TOTAL NOOB.
I HAVE A FEELING
THEY MIGHT HAVE CONVERTED OVER
FROM ANOTHER GAME, THOUGH.
YOU SHOULD SEE
THEIR SKILL STATS.
THEY'RE THROUGH THE ROOF.
YOU KNOW HOW, ON FLOOR 24,
THERE'S THAT TINY, LITTLE ISLAND
JUST NORTH OF THE MAIN TOWN,
THE ONE WITH THE HUGE TREE?
WELL, EVERY DAY AT 3:00,
YOU KNOW WHO SHOWS UP
UNDER THAT TREE
WAITING TO TAKE ON
ANY CHALLENGER ONE‐ON‐ONE.
ZEKKEN STARTED BY POSTING
THIS OPPONENTS WANTED NOTICE
ON THE MMO TOMORROW
BULLETIN BOARD.
FOLKS WANTED TO TEACH THIS
COCKY "A. L. O." NOOB A LESSON,
SO ON THE FIRST DAY,
ABOUT 30 PLAYERS SHOWED UP.
IT DIDN'T GO SO WELL
FOR 'EM, THOUGH.
Asuna: WHAT? THEY LOST?
Lisbeth: ALL OF 'EM,
ONE AFTER THE OTHER.
AND GET THIS.
NONE OF 'EM MANAGED
TO CHIP OFF MORE THAN 30%
OF ZEKKEN'S H. P.
THAT'S A BADASS.
Silica: I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW GOOD ZEKKEN IS.
WHO THOUGHT A NEWBIE TO THE GAME
COULD FLY AS GOOD AS THAT?
IT TOOK ME AT LEAST SIX MONTHS
TO LEARN HOW TO FLY
AND FIGHT AT THE SAME TIME,
AND I'M STILL LEARNING STUFF.
I‐‐I DID IT.
WHAAH!
Asuna: DID YOU
FIGHT ZEKKEN, TOO?
Silica: NOT EVEN. I'M NO DUMMY.
I WATCHED ONE DUEL, AND I KNEW
I DIDN'T STAND A CHANCE.
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT IT WAS LIKE,
WHY DON'T YOU ASK LIZ AND LEAFA?
THEY TOOK ZEKKEN ON YESTERDAY.
THEY FOUGHT AND LOST
LIKE A COUPLE OF CHAMPS.
Lisbeth: PLEASE DON'T REMIND ME.
Leafa: GOOD LEARNING EXPERIENCE,
THOUGH.
Asuna: (LAUGHS)
AH. IT'S SNOWING.
Silica: YEAH. PRETTY, ISN'T IT?
Asuna: SO, ANYWAY,
BACK TO ZEKKEN.
IF THIS PLAYER'S
AS STRONG AS YOU SAY,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THERE ARE
NO MORE CHALLENGERS TO FACE.
Silica: I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
THERE'S A PRETTY COOL PRIZE
ON THE LINE, DON'T YOU KNOW?
Asuna: REALLY? WHAT IS IT,
SOME KIND OF RARE ITEM
OR SOMETHING?
Silica: NOPE.
IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT.
WHOEVER BEATS ZEKKEN WILL GET
AN ORIGINAL SWORD SKILL.
IT'S A SPECIAL MOVE THAT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE SUPER STRONG.
Asuna: AN ORIGINAL SWORD SKILL?
HUH.
WHAT TYPE? HOW MANY HITS?
Silica: MM...
WELL, IT'S A GENERAL SKILL
FOR A ONE‐HANDED SWORD.
OH, BUT HERE'S THE THING.
IT'S AN 11‐HIT COMBO!
Asuna: NO WAY! 11?!
Lisbeth: THE STRONGEST
ORIGINAL SWORD SKILL
BEING USED RIGHT NOW,
HOW MANY HITS DOES IT HAVE?
Leafa: THAT'D BE THE ONE
GENERAL EUGENE DEVELOPED,
THE VOLCANIC BLAZER.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
AN EIGHT‐HIT COMBO.
HE HASN'T PASSED IT ON
TO ANYONE ELSE YET,
AND I DOUBT HE EVER WILL.
Asuna: I GUESS THAT EXPLAINS
WHY SO MANY PLAYERS
KEEP LINING UP
TO CHALLENGE ZEKKEN.
HAVE ANY OF YOU SEEN
THIS SWORD SKILL IN ACTION?
Lisbeth: MM‐MM.
I HEARD ZEKKEN DEMOED IT
ON THE FIRST DAY
OF THE DUELS, THOUGH.
APPARENTLY IT BLEW MINDS
LEFT AND RIGHT,
BUT SINCE THEN, IT HASN'T
BEEN USED IN ANY OF THE FIGHTS.
MAYBE THE REASON FOR THAT'S
'CAUSE THERE HASN'T BEEN
ANYONE TOUGH ENOUGH
TO GET ZEKKEN TO USE IT.
WHOEVER DOES HAS MY RESPECT.
Asuna: LEAFA,
WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN YOU FOUGHT ZEKKEN?
Leafa: BESIDES LOSING?
IT WAS GOING GOOD
TILL OUR H.P.s
DROPPED BELOW 60%, BUT...
IN THE END, ZEKKEN BEAT ME
USING NOTHING
BUT DEFAULT SKILLS.
Asuna: REALLY?
OH! I CAN'T BELIEVE
I ALMOST FORGOT TO ASK.
WHAT'S ZEKKEN'S RACE
AND WEAPON OF CHOICE?
Leafa: AN IMP.
THE MAIN WEAPON'S
A ONE‐HANDED SWORD.
IT'S ABOUT AS SKINNY
AS YOUR RAPIER, ASUNA,
BUT ONLY JUST.
AND ZEKKEN'S SUPER FAST, TOO.
I COULDN'T EVEN SEE
THE ATTACKS COMING AT ME.
THAT'S NEVER HAPPENED
TO ME BEFORE.
I'M STILL KIND OF SHOCKED.
Asuna: A SPEED TYPE, HUH?
IF YOU HAD A HARD TIME
TRACKING ZEKKEN,
I DOUBT I'D BE ABLE TO, EITHER.
AH! I KNOW SOMEONE
WHO MIGHT, THOUGH.
MR. SLEEPYHEAD'S
THE FASTEST PLAYER I'VE SEEN.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
WOULD KIRITO
GO FOR THAT KIND OF CHALLENGE?
Lisbeth and Silica: (LAUGH)
Asuna: WHAT? WHAT'D I SAY?
Leafa: (LAUGHS) NOTHING.
IT'S JUST KAZUTO
ALREADY TRIED IT,
AND, BOY, DID HE
LOSE SPECTACULARLY.
All: (LAUGH)
Asuna: I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WAS HE HOLDING BACK?
Lisbeth: HMM.
KIND OF HARD FOR ME TO SAY.
FROM WHERE I WAS STANDING,
IT LOOKED LIKE IT.
YEAH, BUT THEN I DON'T THINK
I'M REALLY THE BEST PERSON
TO JUDGE
WHETHER HE WAS OR WASN'T.
HE DIDN'T USE
THAT DUAL‐WIELDING TRICK.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
SO I GUESS, IN A WAY,
HE WASN'T GOING ALL OUT.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT KIND OF MAKES SENSE.
I MEAN, IT'S A DUEL
IN A NORMAL GAME.
THERE'S NO REASON
FOR KIRITO TO FIGHT
LIKE HIS LIFE
DEPENDED ON IT ANYMORE.
THE ONLY TIME HE'LL TAKE
A FIGHT SERIOUSLY NOW
IS IF THE GAME
STOPS BEING A GAME,
WHEN THE VIRTUAL WORLD
BECOMES THE REAL WORLD.
IN A WAY, I HOPE
HE NEVER GOES FULL TILT
IN A BATTLE EVER AGAIN.
HE'S KIND OF HAD ENOUGH OF THAT.
I MEAN, HECK,
HE GETS INTO ENOUGH TROUBLE
ON HIS OWN AS IT IS.
Asuna: HEH.
YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
Leafa: WELL,
FROM WHERE I WAS STANDING,
I GOT A DIFFERENT IMPRESSION.
I THINK KAZUTO WAS
DEFINITELY GIVING IT HIS ALL.
HE SEEMED SERIOUS
AND FOCUSED AND DETERMINED.
HE PUT UP A GOOD FIGHT.
AT ONE POINT, THOUGH,
SOMETHING WEIRD HAPPENED.
RIGHT BEFORE THE DUEL WAS OVER,
THEY WERE LOCKING SWORDS,
AND THEN THEY BOTH JUST STOPPED.
IT LOOKED LIKE KAZUTO
WAS SAYING SOMETHING TO ZEKKEN.
I COULDN'T HEAR WHAT
'CAUSE OF ALL THE CHEERING.
AND THEN, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
THEY BACKED OFF FROM EACH OTHER.
ZEKKEN CHARGED HIM.
BUT KAZUTO COULDN'T DODGE IT,
AND THAT'S HOW THE DUEL ENDED.
Asuna: REALLY?
WHAT WERE THEY TALKING ABOUT?
Leafa: I WISH I KNEW.
I ASKED HIM,
BUT KAZUTO WOULDN'T TELL ME.
WHATEVER IT WAS,
IT MUST BE PRETTY IMPORTANT
TO KEEP TO HIMSELF.
Asuna: INTERESTING.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I GUESS THE ONLY WAY
TO FIND OUT WHAT HE SAID
IS TO ASK ZEKKEN MYSELF.
Lisbeth: HUH. YOU THINK
YOU'RE UP TO THE CHALLENGE?
Asuna: I'M NOT DOING IT
'CAUSE I THINK I CAN WIN.
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS ZEKKEN
PERSON INTRIGUES ME, IS ALL.
I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT I THINK
THIS ZEKKEN PERSON'S HERE
FOR REASONS OTHER THAN DUELING.
Lisbeth: YEP,
THAT'S WHAT I THINK, TOO.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO FIND OUT
WHAT IT IS, GET READY,
'CAUSE YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO PUT UP
AS GOOD A FIGHT AS YOUR BOY
KIRITO AND THEN SOME.
Asuna: (LAUGHS)
YEAH, I KNOW.
WILL YOU GUYS COME CHEER ME ON?
‐ All: MM‐HMM.
‐ Silica: YOU KNOW WE WILL.
IT'LL BE AWESOME. WE WOULDN'T
MISS IT FOR ANYTHING.
Lisbeth: WHICH CHARACTER
ARE YOU GONNA DUEL WITH?
YOU STILL HAVE
THE SYLPH ACCOUNT, DON'T YA?
Asuna: HMM.
I GUESS I'LL USE THIS ONE.
IF ZEKKEN'S A SPEED TYPE,
IT'LL PROBABLY COME DOWN
TO WHO CAN HOLD OUT THE LONGEST,
RATHER THAN D. P. S.
AND THAT'S THAT.
SO 3:00 ON THE ISLAND
ON FLOOR 24, RIGHT?
Leafa: MM‐HMM.
Asuna: THEN IF WE MEET HERE
TOMORROW AT 2:30, WE CAN‐‐
OH, NO. IT'S ALREADY 6:00?
I'LL BE LATE FOR DINNER.
Leafa: I GUESS WE MIGHT AS WELL
CALL IT A DAY AND LOG OUT, TOO.
Lisbeth: RICH GIRLS
AND THEIR PROBLEMS. AM I RIGHT?
Silica: (GIGGLES) I CAN'T
BELIEVE HE'S STILL ASLEEP.
Leafa: I KNOW.
HE DIDN'T EVEN FEEL A THING.
‐ Asuna: HEY, LIZ.
‐ Lisbeth: WHAT'S UP?
Asuna: A LITTLE WHILE AGO,
YOU SAID YOU THOUGHT ZEKKEN
CONVERTED OVER TO "A. L. O."
THE WAY YOU DESCRIBED THE DUELS
GOT ME THINKING.
COULD ZEKKEN BE
SOMEONE FROM "S. A. O."?
Lisbeth: UH‐HUH.
THAT'S THE IMPRESSION I GOT
AFTER MY DUEL.
I WANTED A SECOND OPINION,
SO AFTER KIRITO LOST HIS,
I ASKED HIM WHAT HE THOUGHT.
Asuna: SO WHAT DID
KIRITO HAVE TO SAY?
Lisbeth: HE SAID
THAT EVEN THOUGH THE SKILLS
WERE THROUGH THE ROOF,
ZEKKEN'S DEFINITELY NOT
A PLAYER FROM "S. A. O."
THAT'S NOT ALL.
KIRITO ALSO SAID THAT IF ZEKKEN
REALLY WAS FROM "S. A. O.,"
THE DUAL‐WIELDING SKILL
WOULDN'T HAVE GONE TO HIM.
IT WOULD HAVE GONE TO ZEKKEN.
Asuna: (GASPS)