Leafa: KAZUTO!
( CHUCKLES )
Kirito: OKAY, WHAT'S WITH
THAT GOOFY GRIN?
Leafa: WELL...
THIS MORNING,
I JUST SO HAPPENED
TO SEE AN INTERESTING ARTICLE.
AND THEN I NOTICED THAT.
Kirito: OH. ( CHUCKLES )
WOW, WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
SOMEONE'S GOT
A SIMILAR HANDLE.
Leafa: YEAH, EXCEPT
THIS ISN'T SIMILAR.
IT'S EXACTLY THE SAME.
Kirito: IF YOU'RE GONNA
PUT IT THAT WAY,
THEN, YEAH, I GUESS.
ALTHOUGH THAT NAME'S
NOT REALLY THAT UNUSUAL.
I MEAN, MINE'S AN ABBREVIATION.
MAYBE THE KIRITO
IN GGO's NAME IS KIRI‐‐
KIRIGAMINE. YEAH,
TOUGURO KIRIGAMINE OR SOMETHING.
( CHUCKLES )
( CHEWING )
BETTER EAT UP,
OR IT'S GONNA GET COLD.
Kirito: WHO IS HE?
HE'S GOTTA BE ONE
OF THE SURVIVORS FROM "S. A. O."
AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
WE MUST HAVE FOUGHT
AT SOME POINT,
AND I BET WE WERE TRYING
TO KILL EACH OTHER.
‐ Leafa: KAZUTO.
‐ Kirito: ( GASPS )
Leafa: YOU'RE MAKING
THAT SCARY FACE AGAIN.
Kirito: I HOPE IT'S
NOT SCARIER THAN USUAL.
( LAUGHS )
Leafa: LOOK,
I ALREADY KNOW EVERYTHING.
I KNOW YOU CONVERTED KIRITO
FROM "A. L. O." TO "GGO,"
SO JUST DROP THE ACT
ALREADY, OKAY?
COME ON.
DID YOU HONESTLY THINK
I WOULDN'T NOTICE
WHEN YOU SUDDENLY VANISHED
FROM MY FRIEND LIST?
Kirito: I DIDN'T THINK
YOU CHECKED THAT THING
EVERY FIVE MINUTES.
Leafa: I DON'T. I JUST KNEW.
LAST NIGHT,
I GOT THIS WEIRD FEELING
AND CHECKED MY LIST.
WHEN I SAW YOU WEREN'T ON IT,
I HEADED OVER TO YOUR ROOM AND
WAS ABOUT TO BUST THE DOOR DOWN.
I DIDN'T, 'CAUSE I KNEW IT'D
PISS YOU OFF SOMETHING FIERCE.
I ALSO KNEW YOU'D NEVER QUIT
"A. L. O." WITHOUT TELLING ME.
I FIGURED YOU MUST HAVE
A GOOD REASON,
SO I CALLED ASUNA UP
TO SEE IF SHE KNEW ANYTHING.
Kirito: YOU DID?
HUH.
Asuna: SORRY.
I HOPE I'M NOT CALLING YOU
TOO LATE.
Kirito: IT'S OKAY.
I WASN'T SLEEPING.
BESIDES, I‐‐
( SIGHS ) NEVER MIND.
Asuna: HONESTLY.
YOU STARTED TO SAY SOMETHING,
SO JUST GO AHEAD AND SAY IT.
Kirito: I GUESS‐‐
I GUESS I WAS
JUST THINKING ABOUT HOW...
I'D LIKE TO HEAR YOUR VOICE.
Asuna: THAT WASN'T SO HARD.
WHAT'S WRONG?
Kirito: NOTHING'S WRONG.
LONG DAY.
Asuna: DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
IN THE GAME
YOU CONVERTED OVER TO?
Kirito: ( GASPS )
N‐NOTHING HAPPENED.
IT'S JUST...
Asuna: IF THE NEW JOB'S
OVERLOADING YOU, I COULD HELP.
Kirito: THANKS FOR OFFERING.
I GOT IT, THOUGH.
BESIDES, IF YOU CONVERTED OVER,
YOU WOULD GET LONELY.
Asuna: ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
Kirito: YEAH.
I'LL BE BACK BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
Asuna: IF YOU NEED ME,
CALL, OKAY?
Kirito: WILL DO.
GOOD NIGHT.
Asuna: GOOD NIGHT.
Kirito: I CAN'T
DRAG ASUNA INTO THIS.
THAT GUY'S SURE TO SHOW UP
IN B. o. B.'s MAIN TOURNAMENT.
I HAVE TO END THIS.
THIS IS MY PROBLEM, NOT HERS.
‐ Leafa: KAZUTO.
‐ Kirito: ( GASPS )
Leafa: KNOW WHAT ASUNA TOLD ME?
SHE SAID NOT TO WORRY,
'CAUSE ONCE YOU TORE UP "GGO,"
YOU'D BE BACK.
SHE DIDN'T SAY IT,
BUT I KNEW SHE WAS
REALLY WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
THAT MAKES TWO OF US.
LAST NIGHT,
YOU GOT HOME SO LATE,
AND WHEN I SAW YOUR FACE,
I WANTED TO SAY SOMETHING,
'CAUSE YOU LOOKED
ALL FREAKED OUT.
Kirito: I DID? SORRY.
Leafa: I HOPE YOU'RE
NOT DOING ANYTHING CRAZY,
BECAUSE IF YOU ARE,
I COULDN'T BEAR IT
IF SOMETHING HAPPENED TO YOU.
Kirito: I'M GONNA BE FINE.
I PROMISE.
TONIGHT'S THE LAST NIGHT
OF GGO's TOURNEY,
AND AFTER THAT, I'LL BE BACK
TO "A. L. O." AND HERE.
I'LL BE BACK, NO MATTER WHAT,
SO DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
Leafa: 'KAY.
( GIGGLES )
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
Kirito: WHAT?
Leafa: WHEN I WAS
TALKING TO ASUNA,
SHE JUST SO HAPPENED TO TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE GONNA GET
A HUGE CHECK FROM THIS NEW GIG.
Kirito: ( GASPS )
THAT'S RIGHT,
AND WHEN I GET BACK,
I'LL TREAT YOU
TO SOMETHING COOL.
Leafa: SERIOUSLY? IN THAT CASE,
THERE'S THIS AWESOME
NEW NANOCARBON SHINAI
I'VE HAD MY EYE ON.
Kirito: OH. OKAY.
SURE. YOU GOT IT.
( METAL THUNKS )
Sinon: THAT DUMB‐ASS.
HE PISSES ME OFF.
I'M SO MAD, I COULD KILL HIM.
Kyoji: TAKE IT EASY, ASADA.
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET,
BUT IT'S WEIRD
TO SEE YOU THIS WORKED UP.
Sinon: YOU SAW HIM.
HE'S OBNOXIOUS, HE'S COCKY,
AND HE'S A DIRTY LIAR.
HE THINKS HE'S SUCH A BIG SHOT
FIGHTING WITH A SWORD
IN "GGO" OF ALL PLACES.
HE TRICKED ME
INTO THINKING HE WAS A GIRL
AND HAD ME TAKE HIM
TO THE GUN MARKET.
I EVEN HELPED HIM
PICK OUT HIS GEAR.
HE THINKS I'M AN IDIOT.
OH, MAN!
( GROANS )
REALLY PISSES ME OFF.
WHAT'S THAT LOOK FOR?
Kyoji: NOTHING.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST THAT,
LIKE, YOU'RE ACTING
KIND OF STRANGE.
I DON'T THINK YOU'VE
EVER TALKED THIS MUCH
ABOUT SOMEONE ELSE BEFORE.
Sinon: YOU'RE KIDDING. REALLY?
Kyoji: YEAH. I MEAN, YOU DON'T
USUALLY LET PEOPLE GET TO YOU,
YOU KNOW, LIKE THIS.
Sinon: I GET LIKE THIS
WHEN PEOPLE PUSH MY BUTTONS.
Kyoji: YEAH, I GUESS YOU DO.
I KNOW.
HOW 'BOUT WE FIND A FIELD
IN THE GAME AND AMBUSH HIM?
Sinon: HUH?
Kyoji: YEAH. I CAN LURE HIM OUT,
AND THEN YOU CAN SNIPE HIM.
ALTHOUGH, IF YOU WANT
TO GET HIM BACK,
YOU PROBABLY WANT
TO TAKE HIM HEAD‐ON.
EITHER WAY, I KNOW I CAN FIND
A COUPLE MACHINE GUNNERS
TO BACK YOU UP IF YOU WANT.
Sinon: THANK YOU, BUT MM‐MM.
I HAD SOMETHING ELSE IN MIND.
IT'S LIKE, YEAH,
HE PISSES ME OFF,
BUT WHEN HE FIGHTS, AT LEAST
HE SEEMS HONORABLE ABOUT IT.
UNLESS I BEAT HIM
FAIR AND SQUARE,
IT WON'T MEAN ANYTHING.
AND IN TODAY'S FINAL,
I'M GONNA BLOW A HOLE
THROUGH THAT DUMB AVATAR OF HIS
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO.
Kirito: WOULD YOU MIND
SURRENDERING, THEN?
I'M NOT A BIG FAN
OF SLASHING AT GIRLS.
Sinon: ( GROANS )
( GASPS )
JUST YOU WAIT.
I SWEAR I'M GONNA PAY YOU BACK
DOUBLE FOR WHAT YOU DID TO ME.
WHAT? WHAT'S WRONG?
Kyoji: NOTHING.
IT'S JUST THAT...
YOU SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
Sinon: HUH?
WOW. I DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE.
I GUESS IT DIDN'T BOTHER ME,
'CAUSE I WAS SO MAD.
Kyoji: OH.
ASADA...
Sinon: ( GASPS )
W‐WAIT. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
Kyoji: I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
THAT'S WHAT.
YOU'RE NOT ACTING
LIKE YOUR USUAL SELF TODAY.
Sinon: OH.
W‐WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HOW DO I USUALLY ACT?
Kyoji: AS LONG
AS I'VE KNOWN YOU,
YOU'VE BEEN COOL,
CALM, AND LEVELHEADED.
NOTHING GETS TO YOU.
YOU'VE GOT THE SAME PROBLEMS
AT SCHOOL AS ME,
BUT YOU DIDN'T RUN AWAY
LIKE I DID.
YOU'RE, LIKE, REALLY STRONG.
Sinon: BUT I‐I'M
NOT STRONG AT ALL.
YOU KNOW THAT.
I GET FREAKED OUT
WHENEVER I SEE A GUN.
Kyoji: BUT SINON DOESN'T.
SHE'S GOT THAT AMAZING RIFLE
AND KNOWS HOW TO USE IT.
IF YOU ASK ME,
THAT'S WHO YOU REALLY ARE,
AND I KNOW, ONE DAY,
YOU'LL BE LIKE THAT
IN REAL LIFE, TOO.
THAT'S WHY WHEN YOU
GO BALLISTIC OVER THAT GUY,
I START TO WORRY.
WHEN I SEE YOU
LOSE IT LIKE THAT,
I WANT TO HELP YOU.
I'D DO ANYTHING TO HELP YOU!
Sinon: I REMEMBER...
I USED TO BE NORMAL ONCE.
I LAUGHED AND CRIED
JUST LIKE ANYONE ELSE.
I DIDN'T BECOME WHO I AM NOW
BECAUSE I WANTED TO.
( GASPS )
Kyoji: ASADA.
Sinon: ( GASPS )
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
WANTING TO HELP ME,
ESPECIALLY SINCE YOU'RE
THE ONLY ONE IN THE CITY
WHO REALLY UNDERSTANDS
WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
BUT I...
I'M JUST NOT READY TO BE
ANYONE'S GIRLFRIEND YET.
BESIDES, I CAN'T REALLY
FIX WHAT'S BOTHERING ME
UNLESS I DO IT ON MY OWN.
Kyoji: I SEE.
Sinon: UNTIL THEN,
DO YOU THINK
YOU COULD WAIT FOR ME?
THANK YOU.
( SWORDS CLASHING )
Combatants: ( YELLING )
Kirito: ( GASPS )
Player: ( LAUGHING )
Death Gun: WITH THAT NAME
AND YOUR SWORD SKILLS,
ARE YOU THE REAL DEAL OR WHAT?
ARE YOU KIRITO?
Player: ARE YOU KIRITO?
Players: ARE YOU KIRITO?
Player: ARE YOU KIRITO?!
( computer beeping )
Aki: WHAT'S THE MATTER, KIDDO?
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'VE SEEN A GHOST.
Kirito: OH. N‐NO.
IT'S NOTHING.
Aki: YOU GOT A SUPER‐HOT NURSE
SITTING HERE,
OFFERING FREE COUNSELING,
AND YOU'RE GONNA PASS IT UP?
COME ON.
TELL ME WHAT'S BOTHERING YOU.
Kirito: WELL,
SINCE YOU PUT IT THAT WAY,
I GUESS I DON'T REALLY
HAVE A CHOICE, DO I?
UM...
BEFORE YOU CAME
TO THE REHAB UNIT,
YOU WERE IN TRAUMA, RIGHT?
Aki: THAT I WAS.
Kirito: I'VE GOT
A PERSONAL QUESTION,
AND IF YOU DON'T WANT TO ANSWER,
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
OF ALL THE PATIENTS
YOU'VE CARED FOR,
CAN YOU REMEMBER
THE ONES WHO DIED?
Aki: LET'S SEE.
I GUESS IF I THINK ABOUT IT,
I CAN RECALL
THEIR FACES AND NAMES,
EVEN PATIENTS I ONLY SPENT
AN HOUR OR SO WITH IN THE O. R.
MM‐HMM. I REMEMBER.
Kirito: DO YOU EVER WISH
YOU COULD JUST FORGET
ABOUT THOSE PEOPLE?
Aki: HMM. THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.
NOT SURE IF THIS IS AN ANSWER,
BUT IT'S THE BEST I GOT.
I GUESS I THINK IF SOMETHING'S
MEANT TO BE FORGOTTEN,
A PERSON'LL END UP FORGETTING IT
WITHOUT EVEN THINKING
THEY WANT TO.
THAT SAID,
THE MORE A PERSON WISHES
THEY COULD FORGET SOMETHING,
THE STRONGER THE MEMORY BECOMES,
TILL THEY CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT IT.
AND IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN MAYBE SUBCONSCIOUSLY,
WHATEVER THE MEMORY IS,
IT'S SOMETHING
THAT SHOULDN'T BE FORGOTTEN.
Kirito: THEN IF I FORGOT,
I MUST BE A MONSTER.
WHEN I WAS STUCK IN "S. A. O.,"
I TOOK OUT‐‐
NO, I KILLED THREE PEOPLE.
THEY WERE ALL RED PLAYERS,
SO MURDER WAS THEIR BUSINESS,
AND I COULD HAVE
OVERPOWERED THEM
INSTEAD OF KILLING THEM, BUT...
I WENT AHEAD
AND KILLED THEM ANYWAY.
I DID IT OUT OF RAGE,
HATRED, REVENGE.
AND OVER THE PAST YEAR,
I'VE TOTALLY FORGOTTEN
ALL ABOUT THOSE PEOPLE.
EVEN AS I SIT HERE
TALKING ABOUT IT,
I CAN'T REMEMBER
WHAT TWO OF 'EM LOOKED LIKE
OR WHAT THEIR NAMES WERE.
HOW'S THAT POSSIBLE?
IF I CAN FORGET PEOPLE I KILLED,
WHAT'S THAT SAY
ABOUT ME AS A PERSON?
Aki: I'M SORRY, KIRIGAYA.
I GUESS I'M NOT THE AWESOME
COUNSELOR I THOUGHT I WAS.
I WISH I COULD TAKE AWAY
THE BURDEN YOU'RE CARRYING
OR AT LEAST HELP
SHARE THE LOAD OF IT.
WHAT DO I KNOW?
I'VE NEVER EVEN PLAYED
"SWORD ART ONLINE."
WHEN YOU SAY YOU KILLED SOMEONE,
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS,
BUT THERE'S ONE THING I KNOW.
WHEN ALL'S SAID AND DONE,
THE REASON YOU DID WHAT YOU DID
WAS TO SAVE SOMEONE ELSE,
WASN'T IT?
IN THE MEDICAL FIELD,
SOMETIMES WE HAVE TO CHOOSE
WHO TO SAVE.
IT DOESN'T MAKE THE DECISION
TO LET SOMEONE DIE ANY EASIER,
BUT STILL,
IN A LIFE‐OR‐DEATH SITUATION,
EVERYONE'S GOT THE RIGHT
TO CONSIDER THE PEOPLE
THEY CAN SAVE
OVER THOSE THEY CAN'T,
EVEN YOU.
JUST THINK ABOUT THE LIVES
OF ALL THE PEOPLE YOU SAVED,
AND YOU'LL MAKE PEACE
WITH YOUR DECISION.
Kirito: I DON'T KNOW.
I WANT TO BELIEVE YOU, BUT...
I CAN'T. I KILLED PEOPLE.
I KILLED 'EM, AND I CAN'T EVEN
REMEMBER WHO THEY WERE!
DON'T YOU GET IT?
IT'S LIKE I DON'T EVEN CARE
THAT THEY'RE DEAD.
I DON'T DESERVE
TO FIND ANY PEACE!
Aki: IF YOU DIDN'T CARE
ABOUT WHAT YOU DID,
YOU WOULDN'T BE
SUFFERING LIKE THIS.
Kirito: ( CRYING )
Aki: DEEP DOWN, YOU REMEMBER.
AND WHEN THE TIME'S RIGHT,
IT'LL ALL COME BACK TO YOU.
WHEN IT DOES‐‐AND IT WILL‐‐
JUST MAKE SURE YOU REMEMBER
ALL THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE ALIVE TODAY
BECAUSE YOU WERE THERE
TO PROTECT THEM.
( NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE )
Asuna: IF YOU NEED ME,
CALL, OKAY?
Kirito: UM...
THANK YOU,
YOU KNOW, FOR THE PEP TALK.
Aki: SURE. GLAD I COULD HELP.
Kirito: I DON'T THINK
ANYTHING'LL HAPPEN
TILL AFTER 8:00.
I SHOULD BE OUT
BY 10:00 AT THE LATEST.
WELL, HERE I GO.
Aki: OKEYDOKE.
BON VOYAGE, YOU SUPER STUD, YOU.
Kirito: ( GASPS )
LINK START.
Kyoji: ASADA.
Sinon: ( MOANS )
OKAY.
I'M GONNA FIGHT HARD,
AND I WILL BEAT HIM.
LINK START.
Lizard: ( ROARS )
Klein: INCOMING!
Silica: OH, MY GOSH!
KLEIN, ARE YOU OKAY?
Klein: ( CHUCKLES )
COME ON, GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR,
AN INVITATION?
Lisbeth: HE'S BEING
EXTRA MANLY TODAY.
Leafa: YEAH, TELL ME ABOUT IT.
Yui: HANG ON, KLEIN.
WE'RE COMING.
Klein: TAKE YOUR TIME, LADIES.
‐ Lizard: ( GROWLING )
‐ Klein: OH, CRAP!
( GASPS )
( GRUNTS ) POISON GAS!
Silica: HOLD YOUR BREATH!
Klein: ASUNA!
HEY, ASUNA...
NEED A HAND HERE.
ALFHEIM TO ASUNA!
Asuna: ( GASPS )
SOO FILLA HAIL OUSTROO.
Klein: ( LAUGHS )
Asuna: I'M SORRY, GUYS.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO SPACE OUT LIKE THAT.
Klein: NAH, IT'S ALL GOOD.
NO HARM, NO FOUL, RIGHT?
Lisbeth: YEAH.
TODAY'S YOUR BOY'S BIG DAY.
Silica: THAT'S RIGHT,
KIRITO'S TOURNAMENT.
IT'S GONNA START SOON.
Leafa: I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU GUYS,
BUT I SAY WE QUIT EARLY
AND GET OVER TO OUR ROOM
TO WATCH IT.
Klein: I SAY WE USE
THE CASH WE SCORED TODAY
TO BUY BEER AND SNACKS.
Lisbeth: DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
WE'RE GONNA LET YOU
BLOW ALL OUR MONEY ON FOOD?
Klein: ( LAUGHS )
Yui: DON'T YOU WORRY, MOMMY.
DADDY'S GONNA WIN TODAY.
YOU'LL SEE.
Asuna: SURE HE WILL.
NO MATTER WHERE HE GOES,
KIRITO KNOWS
HOW TO HANDLE HIMSELF.
Lisbeth: HEY, GUYS, WE DON'T
WANT TO MISS THE FIRST MATCH.
SO LET'S START HEADING OVER
TO YGGDRASIL CITY.
Asuna: OKAY.
‐ Player 2: HUH?
‐ Player 3: HUH?
Player 4: COME ON, FOLKS.
PLACE YOUR BETS.
Sinon: ( SCOFFS )
Kyoji: SINON!
Sinon: HEY, SPIEGEL.
Kyoji: IT'S ALMOST TIME.
I BELIEVE IN YOU.
I KNOW YOU'RE GONNA WIN
THIS THING.
Sinon: THANKS.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
Kyoji: WELL, I THOUGHT
I'D FIND A BAR SOMEWHERE
AND WATCH THE FEED FROM THERE.
Sinon: COOL.
I'LL TRACK YOU DOWN AFTER THIS,
AND WE CAN TOAST MY VICTORY
OR CRY IN OUR BEERS.
Kyoji: SINON‐‐
I MEAN ASADA...
Sinon: YEAH? WHAT'S UP?
Kyoji: I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU MEANT
WHAT YOU SAID EARLIER.
Sinon: WHAT DID I SAY?
Kyoji: YOU ASKED ME
TO WAIT FOR YOU, REMEMBER?
AFTER YOU WON THIS THING
AND CONQUERED YOUR FEARS, WE‐‐
THEN MAYBE WE COULD
GO OUT AND STUFF.
Sinon: WHAT THE‐‐
YOU'RE BRINGING THIS UP NOW?
Kyoji: IT'S JUST THAT...
I CARE ABOUT YOU SO MUCH, ASADA.
Sinon: DON'T DO THIS NOW.
I HAVE TO FOCUS
ON THE TOURNAMENT.
I'M SORRY, BUT I DON'T
HAVE A CHANCE OF WINNING
UNLESS I PUT EVERYTHING
I'VE GOT INTO IT.
Kyoji: RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
EVEN SO, I BELIEVE IN YOU,
AND I'LL WAIT TILL YOU'RE READY.
Sinon: OKAY.
WELL, UH,
I BETTER GO GET READY NOW.
SEE YA.
Kyoji: I'LL BE ROOTING FOR YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
Sinon: ( SIGHS )
‐ Player 5: WHOA.
‐ Players: ( GASPING )
Sinon: I WON'T LOSE TODAY.
Kirito: I WON'T EITHER.