Asuna: SO ZEKKEN
SHOWS UP AT 3:00
‐ ON THIS ISLAND ON FLOOR 24.
‐ Lisbeth: MM‐HMM.
Asuna: THEN I'LL SEE YOU GUYS
THERE TOMORROW AT 2:30.
‐ Leafa: OKAY.
‐ Lisbeth: YOU GOT IT.
Silica: I CAN'T WAIT.
THIS'LL BE SO MUCH FUN.
‐ Leafa: YEAH, IT WILL.
‐ Lisbeth: HUH. YEAH!
THE BERSERK HEALER'S
GONNA GET UNLEASHED.
Asuna: OH?
Yui: DADDY, YOU HAVE
SOMETHING ON YOUR FACE.
Kirito: HUH? FOR REAL?
Yui: YES. IT'S COVERED IN INK.
‐ Kirito: YOU'RE KIDDING!
‐ Yui: (LAUGHS)
Asuna: SEE YOU GUYS TOMORROW.
‐ Lisbeth: YEAH! SEE YA!
‐ Silica: SEE YA!
Asuna: (SHIVERS)
(DOOR BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEP)
GOOD NIGHT, MS. SADA.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
I'M SORRY
YOU HAD TO WORK SO LATE.
Sada: (SIGHS)
NOT AT ALL, REALLY.
JUST DOING MY JOB, MISS.
Asuna: DO YOU KNOW IF MY MOTHER
AND BROTHER ARE HOME YET?
Sada: KOICHIRO PHONED TO SAY
HE WON'T BE IN
TILL LATE TONIGHT,
AND YOUR MOTHER
IS WAITING IN THE DINING ROOM.
Asuna: OH. THANK YOU.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT, MS. SADA.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Kyoko: YOU'RE LATE.
(CLOCK CHIMING)
NEXT TIME, I WANT YOU HERE
FIVE MINUTES EARLY
Asuna: YES, MA'AM.
(CHAIR CLATTERING)
(GASPS)
IT LOOKS GOOD.
Kyoko: I ASSUME YOU WERE
USING THAT THING AGAIN?
Asuna: YES.
MY FRIENDS AND I WERE
DOING OUR HOMEWORK TOGETHER.
UNLESS YOU ACTUALLY
PHYSICALLY DO YOUR HOMEWORK,
YOU WON'T LEARN A THING.
Asuna: BUT WE ALL LIVE
SO FAR AWAY FROM EACH OTHER.
IT'S MORE CONVENIENT
FOR US TO MEET IN‐GAME.
Kyoko: IT HARDLY
QUALIFIES AS MEETING
IF YOU'RE USING THAT TOY.
BESIDES, DOING YOUR HOMEWORK
IS NOT A TEAM ACTIVITY.
IF YOU'RE WITH YOUR FRIENDS,
YOU'LL JUST FOOL AROUND.
ASUNA, YOU DON'T HAVE TIME
TO PLAY AROUND ANYMORE.
YOU'RE TWO YEARS
BEHIND EVERYONE ELSE.
YOU SHOULD BE STUDYING
AS HARD AS YOU CAN
TO MAKE UP
FOR ALL THAT LOST TIME.
Asuna: BUT I AM STUDYING HARD.
DIDN'T YOU SEE MY GRADES
FOR THE SECOND SEMESTER?
I LEFT THEM ON YOUR DESK.
Kyoko: YES, I SAW THEM,
BUT GRADES FROM A SCHOOL
LIKE THAT ARE SUSPECT, AT BEST.
Asuna: THEY'RE NOT SUSPECT.
Kyoko: YES, WELL,
FOR YOUR NEXT TRIMESTER,
I'VE DECIDED
TO HIRE YOU A TUTOR,
AND NOT ONE OF THOSE VIRTUAL
ONES EVERYONE'S GOING ON ABOUT,
SOMEONE WHO'LL COME
TO THE HOUSE.
Asuna: BUT DON'T I GET
TO HAVE ANY SAY IN IT?
Kyoko: HAVE A LOOK AT THIS.
Asuna: A TRANSFER EXAM
STUDY GUIDE?
Kyoko: I KNOW SOMEONE
ON THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS THERE.
AFTER SOME DISCUSSION,
I CONVINCED THEM
TO LET YOU TAKE AN EXAM
TO TRANSFER
INTO THEIR SENIOR CLASS.
IT'S A PROPER HIGH SCHOOL,
NOT SOME MAKESHIFT STUDY HALL.
AND SINCE IT'S CREDIT‐BASED,
I'M SURE YOU'LL BE
ABLE TO GRADUATE
AFTER THE FIRST TRIMESTER.
IF YOU DO, YOU'LL BE
BACK ON TRACK FOR COLLEGE.
Asuna: WAIT! HOLD ON!
YOU CAN'T JUST MAKE A DECISION
LIKE THIS WITHOUT ME!
I‐I HAPPEN TO LIKE
THE SCHOOL I'M IN.
THE TEACHERS THERE ARE GREAT.
I‐I CAN LEARN THERE
JUST AS MUCH AS ANYWHERE!
I DON'T HAVE TO CHANGE SCHOOLS!
Kyoko: (SIGHS)
I'VE DONE MY RESEARCH,
YOU KNOW, AND BELIEVE ME,
THAT PLACE YOU'RE ATTENDING
CAN HARDLY BE CALLED A SCHOOL.
THE CURRICULUM IS SLAPDASH,
AND THE CLASSES ARE A JOKE.
EVEN THE FACULTY'S SUBSTANDARD.
THEY'RE A BUNCH OF LOSERS
WITH NO REAL CREDENTIALS
TO SPEAK OF.
Asuna: (GASPS)
DON'T SAY THAT.
Kyoko: THEY CLAIM
THEY'RE HELPING THE STUDENTS
WHO FELL BEHIND
BECAUSE OF THAT ACCIDENT.
IT'S ALL A LIE.
THEY JUST WANT ALL THE CHILDREN
WHO'VE SPENT THE LAST TWO YEARS
KILLING EACH OTHER
IN ONE CONVENIENT PLACE
SO THEY CAN MONITOR THEM.
IT'S MORE LIKE AN ASYLUM
THAN A SCHOOL.
Asuna: DID YOU FORGET, MOTHER?
I SPENT TWO YEARS
KILLING OTHER KIDS, TOO.
(GASPS)
Kyoko: ALL THE FRIENDS
YOU HAD BACK IN JUNIOR HIGH
ARE STUDYING TO GET
INTO COLLEGE THIS YEAR.
THEY'RE LEAVING YOU BEHIND.
DOESN'T THAT BOTHER YOU?
Asuna: NOT AT ALL. IF IT TAKES
AN EXTRA YEAR OR TWO,
IT WON'T MAKE MUCH
OF A DIFFERENCE.
BESIDES, I MIGHT NOT WANT
TO GO TO COLLEGE.
Kyoko: RIDICULOUS.
I WON'T ENTERTAIN SUCH TALK.
YOU'RE FAR TOO GIFTED,
AND YOUR FATHER AND I
HAVE GONE TO GREAT LENGTHS
TO NURTURE YOUR TALENTS.
I HOPE YOU APPRECIATE THAT.
Asuna: I DO, BUT SHOULDN'T I GET
TO HAVE A SAY IN MY OWN FUTURE?
SURE, I MIGHT NOT KNOW WHAT KIND
OF CAREER I WANT RIGHT NOW,
BUT I'M CLOSE TO FINDING OUT.
IF I STAY IN MY SCHOOL
FOR ANOTHER YEAR,
IT WILL HELP ME MAKE
THAT DECISION.
Kyoko: (SIGHS)
NO MATTER HOW LONG YOU STAY
AT A PLACE LIKE THAT,
IT'LL JUST LIMIT YOUR OPTIONS.
LOOK, TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO MAKE A WRONG TURN NOW
AND REGRET IT LATER.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO HAVE A GOOD LIFE
AND FIND YOURSELF A GOOD CAREER
YOU CAN BE PROUD OF.
Asuna: SO THAT BOY YOU FORCED ME
TO MEET ON NEW YEAR'S DAY,
THAT WAS YOU TRYING
TO HELP ME WITH MY CAREER?
YOU SHOULD'VE HEARD HIM.
HE WAS TALKING LIKE WE WERE
ALREADY ENGAGED OR SOMETHING.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S LIMITING MY OPTIONS,
NOT ME AND NOT MY SCHOOL!
MARRIAGE IS PART OF YOUR CAREER.
IF YOU MARRY BENEATH YOU
OR MARRY POOR,
I GUARANTEE YOU'LL REGRET IT.
YOU WON'T HAVE
THE MEANS TO PURSUE
WHATEVER IT IS
YOU REALLY WANT TO DO.
THAT'S WHY I THINK YUUYA
WOULD BE AN EXCELLENT CHOICE.
HIS FAMILY OWNS
A SMALL REGIONAL BANK.
THOSE ARE MUCH MORE STABLE
THAN SOME MEGA‐BANK
RUN BY A BOARD OF DIRECTORS.
Asuna: YOUR LAST CHOICE
WASN'T VERY GOOD.
DID YOU FORGET HOW HE MADE ME
AND I DON'T KNOW
HOW MANY OTHERS SUFFER?
NOBUYUKI SUGOU
NEARLY BANKRUPTED RECT.
HE WAS YOUR CHOICE, MOTHER.
Kyoko: ENOUGH, YOUNG LADY!
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ABOUT HIM IN THIS HOUSE AGAIN.
AND YOU'RE WRONG.
IT WASN'T MY CHOICE.
IT WAS YOUR FATHER'S.
HE SUGGESTED THAT CROOK
MARRY INTO THIS FAMILY.
HE'S NEVER BEEN
A GOOD JUDGE OF CHARACTER.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
YUUYA MIGHT LACK INITIATIVE,
BUT HE SEEMS STABLE,
AND STABILITY IS
THE CORNERSTONE OF MARRIAGE.
Asuna: I DON'T CARE.
I HAVE NO INTENTION
TO DATE OR MARRY HIM.
I CHOOSE WHO I'LL MARRY.
Kyoko: FINE.
AS LONG AS THE MAN YOU CHOOSE
IS FROM A GOOD FAMILY
AND IS WORTHY OF YOU.
HOWEVER, A BOY LIKE THAT,
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND FROM SCHOOL,
IS NOT WORTHY.
Asuna: (GASPS)
Y‐YOU HAD HIM INVESTIGATED?
Kyoko: OF COURSE I DID.
TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
YOUR FATHER AND I ONLY WANT
WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU IN LIFE.
YOU HAVE THE POTENTIAL
TO DO WHATEVER YOU WANT
AS LONG AS YOU MAKE
THE RIGHT CHOICES.
Asuna: I NEED TIME
TO THINK ABOUT TRANSFERRING.
Kyoko: KEEP IN MIND
THE DEADLINE'S NEXT WEEK.
DON'T FORGET.
AND AFTER YOU FILL OUT THE FORM,
MAKE THREE COPIES,
AND LEAVE THEM
IN MY OFFICE ON MY DESK.
Asuna: MOTHER...
Kyoko: WHAT IS IT?
Asuna: EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE GONE,
YOU'RE STILL ASHAMED OF GRANDMA
AND GRANDPA, AREN'T YOU?
YOU'RE ANGRY YOU WEREN'T BORN
INTO A RICH, IMPORTANT FAMILY.
Kyoko: (GASPS)
ASUNA, COME BACK HERE RIGHT NOW!
ASUNA!
(ASUNA FLOPS DOWN)
Asuna: KIRITO.
HEY, ABOUT THAT QUESTIONNAIRE,
HAVE YOU FIGURED OUT
WHAT YOU WANNA DO YET?
Kirito: I GUESS, IF ANYTHING,
I WANNA GO FROM PLAYING GAMES
TO BEING A CREATOR.
Asuna: A CREATOR?
WHAT, FOR GAMES?
Kirito: NO, NOT FOR GAMES.
I WANNA MAKE
A HUMAN‐MACHINE INTERFACE
TO REPLACE
THE FULL‐DIVE TECH WE USE NOW.
I'VE BEEN GOING
TO ALL THESE TECH FORUMS
TO LEARN MORE ABOUT IT,
BUT IT'S A HECK OF A LOT
OF INFORMATION TO ABSORB.
Asuna: I WANT TO BE WITH KIRITO
AND GO AFTER THE SAME DREAM,
BUT NOW...
Kirito: YOU SURE ARE STRONG,
WAY STRONGER THAN I AM.
Asuna: I'M NOT STRONG AT ALL.
(SOBS)
IN THAT WORLD, I WAS A WARRIOR,
BUT HERE...
LIGHTNING FLASH ASUNA
OF THE KNIGHTS
OF THE BLOOD OATH IS GONE.
IN THE REAL WORLD,
I DON'T HAVE ANY REAL POWER.
Kirito: HEY.
Asuna: IT'S RARE FOR YOU TO BE
SO PUNCTUAL, DON'T YA THINK?
Kirito: IT HAPPENS SOMETIMES.
Asuna: (SIGHS)
Yui: (SNORING)
Asuna: (GASPS)
(SIGHS)
HEY, YOU REMEMBER?
YOU KNOW, THAT ONE DAY YOU
CAME TO MY PLACE IN SELMBURG
AND I MADE YOU DINNER?
Kirito: HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT MY MEMORY'S ABOUT AS GOOD
AS MY PUNCTUALITY.
Asuna: WHAT?!
Kirito: YEAH. I REMEMBER
THAT DAY LIKE IT WAS YESTERDAY.
Asuna: REALLY?
Kirito: OF COURSE. LET'S SEE.
THAT'S THE DAY I GOT
A SUPER‐RARE FOOD ITEM, RIGHT?
AND YOU MADE
AN AWESOME STEW OUT OF IT.
(SIGHS)
THAT WAS SOME TASTY MEAT.
I'M NEVER GONNA FORGET THAT DAY.
Asuna: (GROANS)
YOU DON'T REMEMBER ANYTHING
EXCEPT THAT STUPID DINNER?!
Kirito: (LAUGHS)
Asuna: (LAUGHS)
IT'S ALMOST TIME.
I BETTER GET OVER THERE.
Kirito: ASUNA,
BE CAREFUL WITH ZEKKEN.
Asuna: HUH?
Kirito: WELL, IT'S LIKE‐‐
ZEKKEN'S REALLY STRONG.
JUST SAYIN'.
Asuna: DON'T YOU WORRY.
LIZ AND THE OTHERS
ALREADY TOLD ME EVERYTHING.
(LAUGHS)
YUP, THEY EVEN TOLD ME
ABOUT HOW YOU LOST.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
OH, BY THE WAY,
LEAFA SAID IN THE MIDDLE
OF YOUR DUEL WITH ZEKKEN,
YOU STOPPED FIGHTING TO TALK.
WHAT'D YOU TALK ABOUT?
Kirito: WELL, ACTUALLY,
I ASKED A QUESTION.
Asuna: WHAT ABOUT?
Kirito: I GOT A WEIRD VIBE,
SO I ASKED...
YOU'RE FULL‐TIME IN THIS WORLD,
AREN'T YOU, ZEKKEN?
AND THEN, FOR AN ANSWER,
I GOT A SLY GRIN
AND A MEGA‐FAST ATTACK.
I'D NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
MOVE THAT FAST.
WHAT DID YOU MEAN BY
"FULL TIME IN THIS WORLD"?
IS THAT THE SAME THING
AS BEING A HEAVY USER?
Kirito: UH‐UH.
ZEKKEN'S WAY DIFFERENT
THAN YOUR AVERAGE,
EVERYDAY HARDCORE GAMER.
IT FELT LIKE‐‐LIKE THEY
WERE A SORT OF PRODUCT
OF THE FULL‐DIVE
ENVIRONMENT ITSELF.
Asuna: I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
Kirito: IN A WAY,
IT'S PROBABLY BETTER YOU DON'T.
THE BEST WAY TO EXPLAIN IT
IS FOR YOU TO EXPERIENCE IT.
Lisbeth: (COUGHS)
EVERY TIME WE TURN AROUND,
YOU'RE ALWAYS
PAWIN' AT EACH OTHER.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOUR LITTLE LOVE‐FEST,
BUT THERE'S A DUEL
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE HAPPENIN'.
‐ Leafa: YEAH.
‐ Silica: YEAH.
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
Asuna: I‐I KNOW.
I WAS ON MY WAY.
Players: (WHOOPING, CHEERING)
(WEAPONS CLASHING)
Player: (SCREAMS)
(GROANS) I YIELD!
I QUIT, RESIGN!
Players: (CHEERING)
Player 2: AH, YEAH!
THAT'S 67 WINS IN A ROW!
Player 3: ZEKKEN'S UNDEFEATED!
Asuna: (GASPS)
Players: (CHEERING)
Player 4: (WHISTLES)
Zekken: HAH!
Asuna: 'SCUSE ME. LIZ...
Lisbeth: WHAT?
Asuna: YOU DIDN'T SAY
ZEKKEN'S A GIRL!
Lisbeth: I DIDN'T?
I COULD'VE SWORN I DID.
Asuna: YOU DIDN'T!
(GASPS)
‐ AND YOU‐‐
‐ Kirito: (GASPS)
Asuna: I HAVE A FEELING
I KNOW WHY YOU LOST NOW.
STARE...
Kirito: MM‐MM.
NO, YOU'RE WRONG.
I DIDN'T GO EASY ON HER
'CAUSE SHE'S A GIRL!
I WAS GOIN' FULL‐OUT! I SWEAR!
HALFWAY THROUGH OUR DUEL,
ANYWAY.
Asuna: WHATEVER!
‐ Lisbeth: (GIGGLES)
‐ Kirito: (SIGHS)
Zekken: SO, UH, IS THERE
ANYONE ELSE OUT THERE
WANNA TAKE ME ON TODAY?
Lisbeth: YOU'RE UP.
GO ON. GET 'ER!
Asuna: WAIT. I GOTTA
PSYCH MYSELF UP FIRST.
Lisbeth: OH, PLEASE!
ONCE YOU CROSS SWORDS WITH HER,
BELIEVE ME,
YOU'LL GET PSYCHED UP.
‐ GO ON! GET IN THERE!
‐ Asuna: (YELPS)
(GASPING)
Zekken: HEY, WHAT'S UP?
YOU NEXT?
Asuna: OH, UH, HI.
I‐I GUESS I AM?
Zekken: AWESOME!
Asuna: (DEEP BREATH)
SO, UH, DOES ANYTHING GO
IN THIS DUEL?
Zekken: OF COURSE.
YOU CAN USE MAGIC OR ITEMS,
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I'M ONLY GONNA USE
MY SWORD, THOUGH.
OH, WAIT. ALMOST FORGOT.
YOU WANNA FIGHT ON THE GROUND
OR IN THE AIR?
Asuna: IS EITHER OKAY?
Zekken: MM‐HMM.
Asuna: HMM.
LET'S DUEL ON THE GROUND, THEN.
Zekken: YOU GOT IT.
JUMPING'S ALLOWED,
BUT NO USING YOUR WINGS, OKAY?
Asuna: "YUUKI."
(DEEP BREATH)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
Lisbeth: HO HO HO.
Asuna: (PANTING)
Yuuki: (GIGGLES)
Asuna: (CHUCKLES)
(THINKING)
SHE IS STRONG,
BUT IF I GAVE UP NOW,
I'D RUIN MY REPUTATION
AS A SWORDSWOMAN.
IN THAT WORLD, I WAS A WARRIOR,
BUT HERE...
(GASPS)
Yuuki: (GASPS)
(CLANG ECHOES)
Lisbeth: (GRUNTS)
Yuuki: (YELLS)
Asuna: (YELLS)
Yuuki: (GRUNTS)
Asuna:
(THINKING) GOT HER.
SHE SAW MY QUADRUPLE PAIN?
Yuuki: (YELLS)
Asuna:
(THINKING) NO WAY.
I WON'T LOSE!
(GASPS)
IS THIS THE 11‐HIT COMBO,
HER ORIGINAL SWORD SKILL?
IF I'M GOING TO LOSE,
IT MIGHT AS WELL BE
TO SOMETHING AS AWESOME AS THAT.
Players: (GASP)
Asuna: (GASPS)
Yuuki: THAT WAS
AN AWESOME FIGHT, GIRL!
YOU'RE DEFINITELY THE ONE.
‐ Asuna: UH, WHAT?
‐ Yuuki: (CHUCKLES)
Asuna: AREN'T WE
GONNA FINISH THE DUEL?
Yuuki: I TOTALLY SEEN ENOUGH
TO KNOW YOU GOT WHAT IT TAKES,
BUT IF YOU WANT,
WE CAN KEEP GOIN'.
Asuna: MM‐MM.
I BEEN LOOKIN' FOR SOMEONE
WHO COULD GO THE DISTANCE.
AT LAST, I FOUND YA!
(GIGGLES)
Asuna: HMM?
WHOA!
Yui: MOMMY.
Lisbeth: ASUNA! WHERE YA GOIN'?!
‐ Leafa: ASUNA!
‐ Silica: ASUNA!
Asuna: UM...
Yuuki: I PICKED YA,
'CAUSE YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN HELP US.
Asuna: HELP? WITH WHAT?