(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Boy: NO, SEE,
THE WAY IT'S SET NOW,
THE GYRO'S TOO SENSITIVE.
IF YOU WANT TO PRIORITIZE
THE VISUAL TRACKING,
YOU GOTTA GIVE YOURSELF
A LITTLE MORE ROOM
IN THESE PARAMETERS.
Kirito: OKAY,
BUT WON'T IT LAG LIKE CRAZY
IF SHE MAKES
ANY SUDDEN MOVES?
Boy: I GUESS YOU'LL
JUST HAVE TO TRUST
THAT THE LEARNING PROGRAM AND
THE OPTIMIZER CAN DEAL WITH IT.
Asuna: HOW MUCH LONGER, GUYS?
OUR LUNCH BREAK'S ALMOST OVER.
Kirito: LET'S JUST SAVE THIS
AS THE DEFAULT SETTING
AND HOPE IT WORKS.
HEY, UH, YUUKI,
CAN YOU HEAR OKAY?
Yuuki: YUP!
I HEAR YOU LOUD AND CLEAR.
Kirito: GOOD.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M FIRING UP THE LENS NOW,
SO IT MIGHT GET BRIGHT.
LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU CAN SEE PERFECT,
AND I'LL LOCK THAT SETTING IN.
Yuuki: FIRE AWAY!
(LENS WHIRS)
HOLD IT.
Kirito: OKAY,
YOU'RE READY TO GO.
LAST THING,
I INSTALLED STABILIZERS,
BUT THEY'RE KINDA JANKY.
TRY NOT TO MAKE
ANY SUDDEN MOVES, 'KAY?
‐ Yuuki: (YELLS, GROANS)
‐ Asuna: THANKS, KIRITO!
Yuuki: WOW.
YOUR SCHOOL'S GINORMOUS.
Asuna: I KNOW, RIGHT?
I'M SORRY I COULDN'T
SHOW YOU AROUND FIRST,
BUT THE LUNCH BREAK'S
ALMOST OVER,
AND WE DON'T WANT TO BE LATE.
Yuuki: NAH, THAT'S OKAY.
I'M JUST EXCITED
TO CHECK OUT YOUR CLASS.
Asuna: SWEET. THEN LET'S
HEAD TO THE FACULTY ROOM
AND INTRODUCE YOU TO MY TEACHER!
Yuuki: (GROANS)
Asuna: WHAT'S WRONG?
Yuuki: IT'S THE ONE PART
OF SCHOOL I DON'T MISS,
GOING TO THE FACULTY ROOM.
Asuna: HEH. DON'T WORRY.
THE TEACHERS HERE AREN'T
YOUR TYPICAL TEACHERS.
THEY'RE COOL.
EXCUSE ME!
‐ Yuuki: M‐ME, TOO!
‐ Asuna: (GIGGLES)
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
IT WAS STILL ALL RIGHT.
Teacher: SURE. I'M FINE WITH IT.
AND WHAT'S THE NAME
OF THE STUDENT
WHO'LL BE JOINING US TODAY?
Yuuki: OH, UM, YUUKI,
YUUKI KONNO, SIR.
Teacher: UH, OKAY.
MS. KONNO, YOU'RE WELCOME
IN MY CLASS ANYTIME YOU WANT.
ALTHOUGH, WE START AKUTAGAWA'S
"A LORRY" TODAY.
UNLESS YOU STICK
WITH IT TO THE END,
YOU WON'T GET THE POINT.
Yuuki: YES, SIR.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
Teacher: MM. HEH HEH.
Asuna: SEE YOU IN CLASS.
Both: (SIGH)
‐ Yuuki: HM?
‐ Asuna: UH...
Both: (LAUGH)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Yuuki: (SIGHS)
Asuna: HEH.
Girls: (LAUGH)
Girl: WHAT'S THAT, MS. YUUKI?
Yuuki: HEY,
HOW'D YOU KNOW MY NAME?
Asuna: NO, SHE WAS USING
MY LAST NAME THERE.
Yuuki: OH, RIGHT. DUH.
Asuna: GUYS, MEET YUUKI KONNO.
SHE'S IN THE HOSPITAL RIGHT NOW
AND CAN'T LEAVE HER ROOM,
SO INSTEAD, SHE'LL BE
ATTENDING OUR CLASS LIKE THIS.
Yuuki: NICE TO MEET YOU!
I CAN ONLY HANG OUT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE, THOUGH.
‐ Students: (GASP)
‐ Boy: COOL.
Girl: NICE TO MEET YOU.
Kota: HEY, THERE.
MY NAME'S KOTA.
Yuuki: OH, HI. HEY.
NICE TO MEET YOU, TOO.
(SCHOOL BELL CHIMING)
Girl 2: PLEASE STAND.
(CHAIRS SCRAPE)
BOW. BE SEATED.
Teacher:
ALL RIGHT THEN, CLASS.
PLEASE OPEN YOUR TEXTBOOKS
TO PAGE NINETY‐SEVEN.
WE'LL BE READING "A LORRY"
BY RYUNOSUKE AKUTAGAWA.
LET'S SEE.
WHO'LL READ IT FOR US?
YUUKI KONNO,
WOULD YOU DO THE HONORS?
‐ Asuna: (GASPS)
‐ Yuuki: HUH? ME?
‐ Asuna: UH...
‐ Students: (MURMURING)
Teacher: PROBLEM?
Yuuki: NO, SIR. I CAN DO IT.
Asuna: YUUKI,
ARE YOU UP FOR THIS?
Yuuki: I MIGHT NOT LOOK IT,
BUT I HAVE READ BEFORE.
(DEEP BREATH)
"WHEN RYOHEI
WAS EIGHT YEARS OLD,
CONSTRUCTION
ON THE LIGHT RAILWAY
BETWEEN ODAWARA
AND ATAMI BEGAN.
EVERY DAY, HE WOULD HEAD
TO THE OUTSKIRTS OF TOWN
TO WATCH THE PROGRESS.
IT WASN'T THE CONSTRUCTION OF IT
THAT FASCINATED HIM SO MUCH.
IT WAS THE SIGHT OF THE LORRIES
TRANSPORTING THE SOIL
WHICH DREW HIM.
THERE WERE TWO LABORERS
ABOARD THE LORRY
STANDING BEHIND THE SOIL
THEY'D JUST LOADED.
SINCE THE LORRY
WAS HEADED DOWN THE MOUNTAIN,
IT DIDN'T NEED
ANYONE TO PUSH IT.
SO AS THE CHASSIS SWUNG
AND THE SLEEVES
OF THE LABORERS' COATS FLAPPED
AND THE NARROW RAILS
BENT UNDER THE STRAIN,
RYOHEI WOULD GAZE LONGINGLY
AT THESE SIGHTS
AND WISH HE COULD
BE A LABORER, TOO,
OR AT THE VERY LEAST,
BE ABLE TO RIDE ON IT
WITH THEM, IF ONLY ONCE."
(SCHOOL BELL CHIMING)
Girl: I LOVED LISTENING
TO YOU READ, YUUKI.
Girl 2: HEY, HAVE YOU HAD
A CHANCE TO TOUR THE SCHOOL?
Girl 3: IF NOT,
WE COULD SHOW YOU AROUND.
Asuna: T‐TAKE IT EASY, GUYS!
Boy: HEY, WANNA GO
TO A SOCCER MATCH?
Yuuki: (GIGGLES) THANKS, GUYS!
YOU'RE THE BEST!
NOW THAT WAS FUN.
Asuna: I KNOW, RIGHT?
Yuuki: THANKS FOR MAKING
TODAY HAPPEN, ASUNA.
REALLY, I HAD A BLAST.
I'M NEVER GONNA
FORGET TODAY EVER.
Asuna: WELL,
OF COURSE YOU WON'T.
THE TEACHER SAID YOU COULD
COME BACK AGAIN IF YOU WANT.
OH, MODERN JAPANESE
IS THIRD PERIOD TOMORROW.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THAT.
Yuuki: YEAH.
Asuna: 'KAY, WHAT'S NEXT?
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
YOU WANT TO DO OR SEE?
Yuuki: OH. UM...
I GUESS THERE IS ONE PLACE
I'D LIKE TO GO.
Asuna: WHERE?
IT'S SO PRETTY HERE, HUH?
JUST LOOK AT THAT SKY.
Yuuki: YEAH.
HEY, ARE YOUR FOLKS COOL
WITH YOU STAYING OUT SO LATE?
YOU'VE BEEN
HAULING ME AROUND ALL DAY.
Asuna: DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT IT.
I SENT THEM A TEXT,
AND IT'S FINE.
WELL? WHERE DO YOU
WANT TO GO NEXT, YUUKI?
Yuuki: GO LEFT.
Asuna: HEY,
ARE WE IN TSUKIMIDAI YET?
Yuuki: YEAH.
NEXT CORNER,
THERE'S A WHITE HOUSE.
CAN YOU STOP THERE?
(SIGHS)
Asuna: YUUKI,
THIS IS YOUR HOUSE, HUH?
Yuuki: MM‐HMM.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D GET
THE CHANCE TO SEE IT AGAIN.
THANKS FOR BRINGING ME OUT HERE
AND FOR EVERYTHING.
Asuna: DO YOU WANT TO GO INSIDE?
Yuuki: NAH. THIS WAS ENOUGH.
COME ON. LET'S HEAD BACK
BEFORE YOUR FOLKS GET WORRIED.
Asuna: NO, IT'S OKAY.
WE CAN STAY A LITTLE LONGER.
Yuuki: ME AND MY FAMILY,
WE ONLY GOT TO LIVE HERE
A LITTLE OVER A YEAR,
AND THE WEIRD THING IS I CAN
REMEMBER EVERY DAY SO CLEAR.
MY SISTER AND ME
USED TO PLAY IN THE YARD,
RUNNING AROUND AND AROUND.
WE HAD BARBECUES,
AND WE EVEN BUILT
THESE BOOKSHELVES WITH OUR DAD.
GOOD TIMES
Asuna: LUCKY YOU.
Yuuki: YEAH. THEY'RE GONNA
TEAR IT ALL DOWN, THOUGH.
Asuna: REALLY? WHY?
Yuuki: MY AUNT WANTS TO EITHER
PUT A CONVENIENCE STORE HERE
OR MAYBE SELL IT.
Asuna: NO WAY.
Yuuki: THAT'S WHY
I WANTED TO COME HERE,
SO I COULD SEE IT
ONE MORE TIME.
Asuna: WELL, I KNOW
HOW YOU CAN SAVE IT.
Yuuki: HOW?
Asuna: YOU'RE FIFTEEN NOW,
AREN'T YOU?
WHEN YOU TURN SIXTEEN,
FIND SOMEONE YOU LOVE,
AND MARRY 'EM!
THAT WAY,
YOU'LL HAVE SOMEONE AROUND
WHO'LL KEEP THIS HOUSE
FROM EVER BEING TORN DOWN.
Yuuki: (LAUGHS)
YOU GOT THE CRAZIEST IDEAS!
(SIGHS)
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANYONE
I WANNA MARRY, THOUGH.
Asuna: OH, YEAH? BUT YOU AND JUN
MAKE A CUTE COUPLE.
Yuuki: GOD, NO!
THAT GUY'S SO IMMATURE.
Asuna: (LAUGHS)
Yuuki: LET'S SEE.
WHO SHOULD I MARRY?
OH, I KNOW!
‐ YOU!
‐ Asuna: HUH?
Yuuki: THE ONLY THING IS,
IF YOU MARRY ME,
YOU'LL HAVE TO BE THE WIFE.
I MEAN, THE OTHER WAY AROUND,
MY NAME'D BE YUUKI YUUKI,
AND THAT'D BE WEIRD.
(LAUGHS)
Asuna: I CAN'T IMAGINE
WHAT MY MOM WOULD SAY.
Yuuki: I KNOW. I'M KIDDING.
'SIDES, YOU ALREADY
GOT SOMEONE LINED UP.
Asuna: OH, WELL, YEAH. I GUESS.
Yuuki: STILL,
YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
I GET THE FEELING
HE'S NOT LIVING
IN THE REAL WORLD, EITHER.
NOT LIKE ME, BUT YOU KNOW.
Asuna: (CHUCKLES)
Yuuki: I CAN'T THANK YOU
ENOUGH, ASUNA.
JUST TO SEE MY OLD HOUSE AGAIN,
YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW HAPPY THAT MAKES ME.
BACK WHEN WE LIVED HERE,
I REMEMBER WE'D GO TO CHURCH
TO PRAY AND STUFF,
AND MOM USED TO ALWAYS SAY THIS
TO ME AND MY SISTER,
"GOD WOULD NEVER PUT US
THROUGH ALL THIS SUFFERING
IF HE DIDN'T THINK
WE COULD BEAR IT."
IT DIDN'T MAKE ME FEEL
ANY BETTER, THOUGH.
INSTEAD OF QUOTING THE BIBLE,
WHAT I REALLY WANTED
WAS FOR MOM TO TALK TO US LIKE‐‐
WELL, LIKE A MOM.
BUT YOU KNOW, AFTER SEEING
OUR OLD HOUSE AGAIN,
I THINK I GET IT NOW.
THE WORDS DIDN'T MATTER.
IT WAS THE FEELING
BEHIND THOSE WORDS.
SHE WAS PRAYING FOR ME SO I
WOULDN'T FEEL SORRY FOR MYSELF,
SO I COULD BE STRONG
'TIL THE END,
AND NOW I FINALLY GET IT.
Asuna: I'M THE SAME.
SEE, I‐‐I HAVEN'T UNDERSTOOD
MY MOM, EITHER.
I CAN'T HEAR WHAT SHE'S
REALLY TRYING TO TELL ME.
SHE CAN'T SEEM TO HEAR ME.
REMEMBER WHAT YOU TOLD ME,
THAT SOMETIMES
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT
TO GET YOUR POINT ACROSS?
HOW CAN I GET TO BE
STRONG LIKE YOU?
Yuuki: ME?
HEH. I'M NOT STRONG. NO WAY.
Asuna: OH, YES, YOU ARE!
YOU'RE NOT LIKE ME.
WHEN YOU STAND UP TO SOMEONE,
YOU DON'T FLINCH
OR LET THEM INTIMIDATE YOU.
NOTHING SEEMS
TO SCARE YOU AT ALL.
IT'S LIKE
SECOND NATURE FOR YOU.
Yuuki: MM, YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN I WAS LIVING
IN THE REAL WORLD OR‐‐
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN‐‐
MOST OF THE TIME,
I WAS FAKING IT.
Asuna: HUH?
Yuuki: IT'S LIKE I THOUGHT
I HAD TO ACT CHEERFUL,
'CAUSE I DIDN'T WANNA MAKE
MY MOM AND DAD FEEL SAD FOR ME.
Asuna: YUUKI.
Yuuki: YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT I THINK IN THE END?
SO WHAT IF I'M JUST ACTING?
IF I GET TO SPEND
MORE TIME SMILING,
EVEN IF IT'S FAKE,
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL? AM I RIGHT?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
I GOT A WHOLE LOT OF TIME LEFT,
AND IT'D BE A SHAME
TO WASTE WHATEVER I DO GOT
BY MOPING AROUND ALL THE TIME,
SO NOW I SAY EXACTLY
WHAT I FEEL TO EVERYONE,
AND IF THEY GOT A PROBLEM
WITH THAT, WHO CARES?
AT LEAST I SPOKE MY MIND
AND MAYBE EVEN
GOT A LITTLE CLOSER TO 'EM.
Asuna: YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S THE REASON
WE'RE HERE TODAY,
WHY WE'RE SO CLOSE
AFTER ONLY A FEW DAYS.
IT'S ALL 'CAUSE OF YOU.
Yuuki: NOPE,
THAT WASN'T 'CAUSE OF ME.
Asuna: HUH?
Yuuki: IT'S 'CAUSE
EVEN AFTER I RAN AWAY FROM YOU,
YOU TRACKED ME DOWN.
LOOK, HOW 'BOUT YOU TRY TALKING
TO YOUR MOM LIKE YOU DID TO ME?
IF YOU TRY
TELLING HER HOW YOU FEEL,
MAYBE YOU'LL
GET THROUGH TO HER.
Asuna: (SIGHS)
Yuuki: DON'T WORRY.
YOU CAN DO IT.
YOU'RE WAY STRONGER
THAN ME, HONEST!
Asuna: (GASPS)
YUUKI.
Yuuki: YOU HIT ME
WITH EVERYTHING YOU HAD.
THAT'S HOW I KNEW I COULD
TRUST YOU WITH EVERYTHING I HAD.
IN THE END, IT WORKED OUT
FOR BOTH OF US, DIDN'T IT?
Asuna: YES, IT DID.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, YUUKI.
Yuuki: (CHUCKLES)
Asuna: (SIGHS)
Yuuki: IF YOU TRY
TELLING HER HOW YOU FEEL,
MAYBE YOU'LL
GET THROUGH TO HER.
DON'T WORRY.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
Kyoko: COME IN.
(TYPING)
(SIGHS)
YOU'RE LATE AGAIN.
Asuna: I'M SORRY.
Kyoko: WELL, IF YOU'RE HUNGRY,
YOU'LL HAVE TO MAKE DO
WITH WHATEVER'S IN THE FRIDGE.
OH, AND DON'T FORGET,
THE DEADLINE
FOR YOUR TRANSFER APPLICATION
IS DUE TOMORROW.
MAKE SURE
IT'S FILLED OUT BY MORNING.
Asuna: ACTUALLY, ABOUT THAT...
Kyoko: HM?
Asuna: WE NEED TO TALK, MOTHER.
Kyoko: WELL, WHAT IS IT?
Asuna: I CAN'T
REALLY EXPLAIN IT HERE.
Kyoko: OKAY, THEN.
WHERE SHALL WE GO?
Asuna: THE VIRTUAL WORLD.
IT'LL ONLY BE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE,
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO USE THIS.
Kyoko: DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
IF YOU CAN'T TELL ME WHAT THIS
IS ABOUT LIKE A NORMAL PERSON,
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
Asuna: BUT YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY I CAN EXPLAIN!
IT'S JUST FIVE MINUTES!
MOM, PLEASE!
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY TO TELL YOU
WHAT I'M THINKING
AND HOW I'M FEELING, HONEST!
I CAN'T TELL YOU
ANY OF THAT HERE!
JUST THIS ONCE.
MOM, ALL I WANT IS
FOR YOU TO SEE MY WORLD!
Kyoko: (SIGHS)
FIVE MINUTES.
Asuna: (GASPS)
Kyoko: BUT NO MATTER
WHAT YOU SAY,
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF ALLOWING YOU
TO ATTEND THAT SCHOOL AGAIN
NEXT YEAR, UNDERSTOOD?
ALSO ONCE YOU'RE DONE, YOU WILL
FILL OUT THAT APPLICATION.
Asuna: OKAY.
Kyoko: SO HOW DO I
USE THAT THING?
Asuna: JUST SIT BACK AND RELAX.
ONCE I TURN IT ON,
IT'LL AUTOMATICALLY CONNECT YOU
TO MY SUB‐ACCOUNT IN THE GAME.
AFTER YOU'RE IN, WAIT FOR ME.
I'M TURNING IT ON NOW.
LINK START.
Kyoko: THIS IS SO BIZARRE.
SEEING A STRANGE FACE MIMIC
WHAT I DO IS UNSETTLING.
AND THIS BODY, IT'S SO LIGHT.
Asuna: OH, THAT'S NORMAL.
THAT PARTICULAR AVATAR'S
WEIGHT SETTING
IS ABOUT NINETY POUNDS OR SO.
FEELS LIGHTER
THAN YOUR REAL BODY, HUH?
Kyoko: THAT IS SO RUDE!
I DO NOT APPRECIATE
WHAT YOU'RE IMPLYING.
THAT'S INTERESTING.
YOUR FACE HERE
LOOKS JUST LIKE YOUR REAL ONE.
Asuna: WELL, YES.
Kyoko: ACTUALLY, I TAKE IT BACK.
YOUR REAL FACE
IS PUFFIER THAN THIS ONE.
Asuna: OH, NOW WHO'S BEING RUDE?
I LOOK THE SAME HERE
AS I DO THERE.
Kyoko: WELL, I'M HERE. NOW WHAT?
YOU DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME LEFT.
Asuna: FOLLOW ME, MOM.
YOU SEE? IT LOOKS JUST LIKE IT.
Kyoko: I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU MEAN.
ALL I SEE IS
SOME OLD CEDAR GRO‐‐(GASPS)
Asuna: DOESN'T IT
BRING BACK MEMORIES
OF THE HOUSE
THAT GRANDMA AND GRANDPA HAD?
I REALLY LOVED
THEIR PLACE IN MIYAGI.
IT WAS MAGICAL.
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
REMEMBER THAT OBON HOLIDAY
WHEN I WAS TWELVE?
YOU, DAD, AND KOICHIRO
WENT TO THE YUUKI
FAMILY COMPOUND IN KYOTO,
AND I WENT TO MIYAGI BY MYSELF.
Kyoko: I REMEMBER.
Asuna: WHEN I GOT THERE,
I APOLOGIZED TO THEM
THAT YOU COULDN'T BE WITH US.
I FELT BAD YOU COULDN'T VISIT
OUR ANCESTORS' GRAVES.
Kyoko: I WANTED TO,
BUT THAT YEAR,
THE YUUKIS WERE HAVING
AN IMPORTANT MEMORIAL SERVICE.
Asuna: NO, MOM,
I'M NOT BLAMING YOU OR ANYTHING.
IN FACT, YOU KNOW
WHAT GRANDPA SAID?
HE SAID NOT TO FUSS,
BECAUSE HE AND GRANDMA
WERE SO PROUD OF YOU.
Kyoko: (GASPS)
YOU LEFT THIS VILLAGE,
WENT TO UNIVERSITY,
BECAME A SCHOLAR,
AND GOT YOUR WORK PUBLISHED.
IT MADE HIM SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU
MAKE A NAME FOR YOURSELF
IN THE WORLD.
AND THEN HE TOLD ME
SOMETHING I'LL NEVER FORGET,
THAT SOMEDAY YOU MIGHT GET TIRED
FROM ALL THE HARD WORK YOU DO
AND NEED A BREAK FROM IT,
AND IF THAT DAY EVER CAME,
HE SAID HE WANTED TO MAKE SURE
THE HOUSE AND THE MOUNTAIN
WERE ALWAYS THERE,
THAT HE'D GUARD THEM
TO GIVE YOU A PLACE
TO COME HOME TO
IF YOU NEEDED IT.
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND IT THEN,
BUT NOW, AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED TO ME,
I THINK I FINALLY DO.
LIFE ISN'T JUST ABOUT DOING
THE THINGS THAT MAKE YOU HAPPY.
IT'S ALSO
ABOUT FINDING A WAY TO LIVE
WHERE THE HAPPINESS OF EVERYONE
AROUND YOU FULFILLS YOU, TOO.
SOMEHOW, I WANT TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO LIVE A LIFE
THAT MAKES
EVERYONE AROUND ME HAPPY.
I WANT A LIFE
THAT LETS ME BE THERE
FOR THE PEOPLE I CARE ABOUT WHEN
THEY NEED SOMEONE TO LEAN ON.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
MOTHER, I'LL STUDY
AND WORK HARD,
BUT I WANT TO KEEP GOING
TO THE SCHOOL THAT I LOVE.
Asuna: (GASPS)
MOM.
Kyoko: (GASPS)
WHAT IS THIS?
THIS IS CRAZY.
I'M NOT REALLY CRYING.
Asuna: MOM.
YOU CAN'T HIDE IT
WHEN YOU'RE SAD IN THIS WORLD.
WHEN YOU CRY,
YOU CRY JUST LIKE IN REAL LIFE.
Kyoko: SUCH AN ANNOYING WORLD.
(CRYING)
Asuna: MORNING, MOM.
Kyoko: MORNING.
ASUNA, ARE YOU
DETERMINED TO LIVE
THE KIND OF SELFLESS LIFE
YOU SPOKE OF?
Asuna: MM‐HMM.
Kyoko: FINE.
IF THAT IS WHAT YOU WANT,
YOU'LL HAVE TO BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO CARRY THAT BURDEN,
SO MAKE SURE YOU GO TO COLLEGE,
AND FOR THAT,
YOU'LL HAVE TO GET BETTER GRADES
THIS TRIMESTER AND NEXT YEAR.
Asuna: (GASPS)
REALLY?
THEN I CAN STAY?
Kyoko: THAT'S UP TO YOU.
YOU'LL HAVE TO PROVE YOURSELF.
DO YOUR BEST.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Asuna: THANKS, MOM. I WILL.
THANK YOU, YUUKI.
HERE I GO.