Both: (GASP)
Kirito: FIVE MINUTES TO GO.
Sinon: WE HAVE TO HURRY.
THIS WAY.
Kirito: (GASPS)
Sinon: HEY, COME ON.
Kirito, thinking: I WONDER IF
ONE OF THESE GUYS IS DEATH GUN.
Sinon: HERE WE ARE.
THIS IS WHERE WE HAVE
TO SIGN UP FOR THE TOURNEY.
IT'S A TYPICAL, RUN‐OF‐THE‐MILL
TOUCH‐PANEL INTERFACE.
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT,
OR YOU WANT SOME HELP?
Kirito: NO, I CAN FIGURE IT OUT.
Sinon: COOL. I'M GONNA BE
OVER AT THE NEXT TERMINAL,
SO IF YOU GET STUCK, HOLLER.
Kirito: OKAY. THANKS A LOT.
HUH?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO ENTER
OUR REAL‐LIFE INFO?
HMM.
‐ Sinon: YOU DONE YET?
‐ Kirito: (GASPS)
YES, I'M ALL DONE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR ALL YOUR HELP TODAY.
SORRY FOR ALL THE TROUBLE.
Sinon: NO WORRIES.
THAT CRAZY RIDE ON THE BUGGY
MORE THAN MADE UP FOR IT.
ANYWAY, WHICH BLOCK DID YOU
END UP WITH FOR THE PRELIMS?
Kirito: UM...
"F," I GUESS, F‐37.
Sinon: OH, REALLY?
I'M IN "F," TOO, NUMBER 12.
THAT'S KIND OF
A COOL COINCIDENCE, HUH?
WHEN DO WE MEET, THOUGH?
OH, GOOD. WE'RE NOT GONNA
MEET UP AGAIN TILL THE FINALS.
Kirito: I'M NOT SURE
WHAT YOU MEAN. WHY IS THAT GOOD?
Sinon: IF A PLAYER MAKES IT
TO THE FINAL BRACKET
IN THE PRELIMS,
IT WON'T MATTER IF THEY LOSE.
THEY'LL AUTOMATICALLY ADVANCE
TO THE BATTLE ROYALE.
THAT MEANS WE BOTH HAVE A SHOT
AT ADVANCING
TO THE BATTLE ROYALE
AS LONG AS WE MAKE IT
TO THE LAST BRACKET.
Kirito: OH.
Sinon: BUT IF WE DO MEET
IN THE FINAL BRACKET
OF THE PRELIMS,
I'LL BE PLAYING TO WIN.
Kirito: OH. I GET IT.
ALL RIGHT, IF WE BOTH MAKE IT,
NO HOLDING BACK.
WOW. I'M IMPRESSED.
THE JAPANESE TRANSLATION ON
THESE TERMINALS IS PRETTY GOOD.
THE OFFICIAL SITE
WAS ENGLISH ONLY.
Sinon: WELL, ZASKAR,
THE COMPANY THAT DEVELOPED
AND RUNS THE GAME, IS AMERICAN.
THEY PROBABLY HAVE SOME JAPANESE
STAFF TO RUN JAPAN'S SERVER.
OH, AND GET THIS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU KNEW,
BUT "GGO" OPERATES AN ILLEGAL
GRAY ZONE HERE AND IN THE U. S.
Kirito: 'CAUSE OF ITS
CASH‐CONVERSION SYSTEM, RIGHT?
Sinon: (CHUCKLES)
YOU WON'T FIND ANYTHING
ON THE COMPANY'S HOME PAGE
EXCEPT
THE MOST BASIC INFORMATION,
AND AS FOR MANAGING
YOUR CHARACTER
OR ACCESSING
YOUR E‐MONEY ACCOUNT
TO CONVERT WHAT YOU EARN,
ANY AND ALL
GAME‐RELATED PROCEDURES
HAVE TO BE DONE IN THE GAME.
Kirito: IT'S AMAZING,
SHADY, BUT AMAZING.
Sinon: IT IS.
THE GAME'S PRACTICALLY
INDEPENDENT OF THE REAL WORLD.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY
THE PERSON I AM IN HERE
AND THE REAL ME FEEL LIKE
TWO DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
SORRY. I DON'T KNOW
WHY I WENT THERE.
WE SHOULD START HEADING OVER
TO THE PRELIM AREA NOW.
YOU READY TO GO?
‐ Kirito: SURE.
‐ Sinon: THAT WAY.
IT'S IN THE BASEMENT.
Kirito: (GASPS)
Sinon: SOMETHING WRONG?
Kirito: HUH? NO, NOTHING.
Sinon: GOOD.
LET'S GO
TO THE WAITING ROOM FIRST.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED SOME PRIVACY
TO CHANGE
INTO YOUR NEW COMBAT SUIT.
Kirito: RIGHT.
(GASPS)
Sinon: (SIGHS)
I SWEAR,
WHAT A BUNCH OF DUMB‐ASSES.
Kirito: HUH? WHO DO YOU MEAN?
THOSE TOUGH‐LOOKING GUYS
OUTSIDE?
Sinon: YEAH, THEM.
IT'S A HALF‐HOUR
BEFORE THE MATCH,
AND THEY'RE OUT THERE
SHOWING OFF THEIR MAIN WEAPONS.
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE ASKING YOU
TO COME UP
WITH A COUNTERMEASURE.
Kirito: OH.
YEAH, THAT IS SILLY.
Sinon: PIECE OF ADVICE,
DON'T EQUIP YOUR PHOTON SWORD
AND FIVE SEVEN
TILL JUST BEFORE
YOUR MATCH STARTS.
Kirito: MM‐HMM.
(GASPS)
Sinon: HUH?
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
HURRY UP,
AND GET CHANGED ALREADY.
Kirito: UH, YES.
I MEAN, I CAN'T.
I MEAN I CAN'T CHANGE NOW!
I‐‐I MEAN‐‐
I'M SORRY!
Sinon: WHY?
Kirito: I HAVEN'T
INTRODUCED MYSELF.
THIS IS WHO I REALLY AM.
Sinon: OKAY.
KIRITO. HUH.
WELL, IT'S AN INTERESTING NAME.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
WAIT.
MALE?! BUT...
I‐‐YOU‐‐
YOU'RE A‐‐YOU'RE KIDDING.
NO WAY.
YOU'RE A GUY?
WITH THAT AVATAR?!
UH...
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: (GROWLS)
WHY, YOU...
(SLAP)
STOP FOLLOWING ME.
Kirito: BUT I'M NOT SURE
WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO DO
AFTER THIS.
Sinon: STOP FOLLOWING ME.
Kirito: OKAY,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
ANYONE ELSE HERE.
Sinon: STOP FOLLOWING ME.
Kirito: BUT‐‐BUT I...
Sinon: (INHALES)
(EXHALES)
(GROANS)
I'LL EXPLAIN IT,
BUT JUST THE BARE MINIMUM.
THAT'S IT. AFTER THAT,
YOU AND ME ARE ENEMIES.
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
THANKS. I APPRECIATE IT.
Sinon: YEAH, WELL,
JUST SO WE'RE CLEAR,
THIS DOESN'T MEAN I FORGIVE YOU.
YOU SEE THAT CLOCK UP THERE?
WHEN IT HITS ZERO,
EVERYONE HERE WILL AUTOMATICALLY
BE TRANSFERRED TO A BATTLEFIELD.
ALONG WITH WHOEVER THEIR
FIRST‐ROUND OPPONENT'S GONNA BE.
YOU WITH ME SO FAR?
Kirito: UH, YEAH.
Sinon: THE FIELD'S A SQUARE.
EACH SIDE'S A KILOMETER.
THE WEATHER, TERRAIN, AND TIME
ARE ALL RANDOMLY GENERATED.
YOUR OPPONENT'S PLACED
500 METERS AWAY FROM YOU.
WHOEVER WINS THE MATCH
GETS TRANSFERRED BACK HERE.
THE LOSER'S TRANSFERRED
TO THE FIRST‐FLOOR HALL,
AND YOU DON'T GET PENALIZED
FOR LOSING A MATCH.
THERE ARE SIXTY‐FOUR PEOPLE
IN BLOCK "F,"
SO FIVE WINS
WILL TAKE YOU TO THE FINAL,
AND YOU'LL BE ELIGIBLE
FOR THE BATTLE ROYALE.
THAT'S IT. NO MORE QUESTIONS.
I'M DONE HELPING YOU.
Kirito: I THINK
I GOT THE GIST OF IT,
AND THANKS AGAIN.
Sinon: HMPH.
YOU BETTER REACH THE FINALS,
'CAUSE EVEN AFTER EVERYTHING
I TAUGHT YOU TODAY,
THERE'S ONE THING LEFT
FOR YOU TO LEARN.
Kirito: YEAH? WHAT?
Sinon: THE TASTE
OF THE BULLET THAT BEATS YOU.
Kirito: I'LL LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, THOUGH?
YOU THINK YOU'LL MAKE IT
TO THE FINALS?
Sinon: HEH. I'LL RETIRE IF I
GET KNOCKED OUT OF THE PRELIMS.
BUT I WON'T.
NOT THIS TIME.
THIS TIME, I'LL KILL
ALL THE STRONG PLAYERS.
HEH.
SINCE THIS IS THE LAST TIME
WE'LL BE CHATTING LIKE THIS,
YOU SHOULD KNOW MY NAME.
THERE IT IS,
THE NAME OF THE PERSON
WHO'S GONNA BEAT YOU.
Kirito: SINON.
I'M KIRITO.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
Sinon: (SCOFFS)
Kirito: (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Spiegel: HEY.
ABOUT TIME YOU SHOWED UP.
I COULDN'T FIND YOU ANYWHERE,
AND I WAS WORRIED
YOU WEREN'T GONNA MAKE IT.
Sinon:
SORRY ABOUT THAT, SPIEGEL.
I TOTALLY LOST TRACK OF TIME
THANKS TO AN UNEXPECTED CHORE.
HEY, HANG ON.
YOU SAID YOU WEREN'T COMPETING.
DID YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND?
Spiegel: WELL, EVEN THOUGH
I KNOW HOW MUCH IT BUGS YOU,
I THOUGHT I'D SORT OF
CHEER YOU ON FROM THE SIDELINES.
I ALREADY PICKED OUT A SPOT
IN FRONT OF THE JUMBO SCREEN
AND EVERYTHING.
WHAT WAS THAT UNEXPECTED CHORE
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT?
Sinon: OH, NOTHING.
I WAS JUST GIVING THIS PERSON
A SORT OF ORIENTATION.
Kirito: THAT'D BE ME.
HI. HOW'S IT GOING?
Spiegel: OH, HI.
IT'S, UH, NICE TO MEET YOU.
SO, UH, ARE YOU
A FRIEND OF SINON'S?
Sinon: HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT SHE'S A DUDE.
Kirito: YEAH.
MY NAME'S KIRITO.
I'M A DUDE.
Spiegel: A‐‐A GUY?
THEN DOES THAT MEAN HE'S A‐‐
THAT YOU'RE‐‐
Kirito: NOT EVEN.
HEY, SINON, THANKS FOR
SHOWING ME A GOOD TIME.
IT WAS A GREAT FIRST DATE.
Sinon: WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU SAYING?
IT WASN'T A GOOD TIME,
AND IT WAS NOT A DATE.
IT WAS A MISTAKE,
SO FORGET MY NAME,
AND FORGET WE EVER MET.
Kirito: OH, COME ON.
DON'T BE SO HEARTLESS.
Sinon: HEARTLESS, MY ASS.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW YOU.
Kirito: BUT WE SPENT
THE WHOLE DAY TOGETHER
PICKING OUT ALL MY GEAR.
Sinon: YEAH,
BUT ONLY 'CAUSE YOU LI‐‐
Announcer: THANK YOU
FOR YOUR PATIENCE, PLAYERS.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY,
BECAUSE THE THIRD
BULLET OF BULLETS
PRELIMINARY TOURNAMENT
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
WHEN THE COUNTDOWN CLOCK
REACHES ZERO,
ALL COMPETING PLAYERS WILL BE
AUTOMATICALLY TRANSPORTED
TO THEIR RESPECTIVE
FIRST‐ROUND FIELD MAPS.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU ALL.
‐ Players: (CHEERING)
‐ (GUNS FIRING)
Sinon: YOU BETTER
MAKE IT TO THE FINALS,
'CAUSE I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO BLOWING YOUR HEAD OFF.
Kirito: I ACCEPT THE INVITATION,
BUT DON'T KEEP ME
WAITING TOO LONG.
Sinon: (GASPS) WHY, YOU...
Kirito: HEH.
Sinon: (GROWLS)
Kirito: MAYBE I WENT
A LITTLE TOO FAR THERE.
Sinon: THIS TIME, I'LL KILL
ALL THE STRONG PLAYERS.
Kirito: IS THAT POSSIBLE?
COULD SHE BE DEATH GUN?
I SAW TWO SIDES OF HER,
BUT WHICH IS THE REAL SINON?
I WON'T FIND OUT
STANDING HERE,
THINKING ABOUT IT.
BUT IF WE CROSSED SWORDS‐‐
I MEAN TRADED SHOTS,
I'M SURE I'LL FIND THE ANSWER.
Kirito: (GASPS)
I CAN'T DODGE ALL THOSE BULLETS.
AT THIS RATE,
I'LL NEVER GET CLOSER TO HIM.
MAYBE IF I COULD USE
MY SWORD TO DEFLECT THE BULLETS,
I COULD GET CLOSER.
THEY'RE FLYING
TOO DAMN FAST, THOUGH.
THERE'S NO WAY I CAN PREDICT
THE TRAJECTORY OF EACH BULLET.
NO, I CAN DO THIS.
THE BULLET LINES TELL ME
EXACTLY WHAT PATH
THE BULLETS ARE TRAVELING.
(GRASS RUSTLING)
(GASPS) NOW!
Uemaru: HOLY CRAP!
Kirito: JUST A LITTLE FURTHER.
Uemaru: (SCREAMING)
Kirito: (GROANS)
DAMN IT.
OH, MAN.
(FANFARE PLAYING)
I CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE
TO DO THIS FOUR MORE TIMES.
I WONDER WHERE SINON IS.
Death Gun:
ARE YOU THE REAL DEAL?
Kirito: THE REAL DEAL?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
WHO ARE YOU?
Death Gun: I SAW YOUR MATCH.
YOU TOOK HIM OUT WITH A SWORD.
Kirito: YEAH. SO WHAT?
IT'S NOT AGAINST THE RULES,
IS IT?
Death Gun: I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN.
ARE YOU THE REAL DEAL?
Kirito: WAIT.
DOES HE KNOW ME?
NO WAY.
WE HAVE MET BEFORE.
WE'VE BEEN FACE‐TO‐FACE
LIKE THIS,
BUT WHERE?
WHERE DO I KNOW HIM FROM?
Death Gun: WITH THAT NAME
AND YOUR SWORD SKILLS,
ARE YOU THE REAL DEAL OR WHAT?
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
Kirito: IF HE KNOWS ME,
I SHOULD KNOW HIM.
THAT'S IT.
HE'S AN "S. A. O." SURVIVOR.
WHO IS HE,
AND WHERE DID WE MEET
IN "S. A. O."?
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)