Asuna: UM, OKAY, EVERYONE!
A TOAST TO THIS GATHERING
OF FRIENDS, NEW AND OLD.
TO US!
All: TO US!
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Silica: WITH EVERYONE HERE,
WE'D BE AN AMAZING PARTY.
Jun: YEAH, WE WOULD. I KNOW!
WE SHOULD RAID THE BOSS
ON FLOOR TWENTY‐THREE.
Klein: I'M DOWN WITH THAT!
Jun: THEN LET'S GO GET HIM!
Klein: YEAH! (LAUGHS)
(PLAYERS YELLING)
Kirito, Klein, and Yui:
YOU'RE GOIN' DOWN!
‐ (FANFARE PLAYING)
‐ (CHEERING)
Both: (LAUGH)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE)
‐ Nori: AWW.
‐ Leafa: (LAUGHS)
Silica: (GROANS)
Sinon: (GIGGLES)
Yuuki: (YELLS)
(GASPS)
Kirito: CRAP.
Yuuki: (YELLS)
HMPH.
(GASPS)
Spectators: (CHEERING)
Nori: YEAH! (LAUGHS)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Siune: NICE GOING, YUUKI!
Tecchi: UNDEFEATED!
(MUSIC, SINGING CONTINUE)
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(RINGTONE CHIMES)
Asuna: (GASPS)
(DOOR CHIME RINGS)
Dr. Kurahashi:
THANK GOODNESS. YOU MADE IT.
ABOUT FORTY MINUTES AGO,
HER HEART STOPPED,
BUT ONLY FOR A MOMENT.
WE GOT IT GOING
WITH DEFIBRILLATION AND MEDS,
BUT IF IT HAPPENS AGAIN...
Asuna: WHY NOW?
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
SHE SEEMED FINE!
Dr. Kurahashi: I'M SORRY.
THE TRUTH IS,
EVER SINCE JANUARY,
WHEN YOU FIRST
CAME TO VISIT HER,
HER CONDITION'S
BEEN TOUCH AND GO,
AND FOR THESE LAST THREE MONTHS,
WE'VE ALL BEEN STUNNED
BY HOW YUUKI'S
MANAGED TO HANG IN THERE.
SHE CAN'T BEAT THIS,
BUT SHE KEEPS FIGHTING.
SHE KEEPS ON FIGHTING.
THE FIFTEEN YEARS YUUKI'S
SPENT ON THIS PLANET
HAVE BEEN ONE LONG BATTLE.
THE H. I. V.'s ONLY PART OF IT.
SHE'S ALSO BEEN FIGHTING
THE HARSH REALITY
OF HER SITUATION
WHILE IN TREATMENT.
THERE'S NO DOUBT THE CLINICAL
TRIALS WITH THE MEDICUBOID
CAUSED HER
AN UNIMAGINABLE AMOUNT OF PAIN,
AND STILL SOMEHOW
YUUKI KEEPS HANGING ON.
WELL, ANYWAY, WE SHOULD
LET HER GET SOME REST NOW.
Asuna: COME ON, YUUKI.
YOU CAN'T LOSE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE ZEKKEN...
THE ULTIMATE SWORDSWOMAN.
(GASPS)
Dr. Kurahashi:
TAKE HER HAND.
IT'S OKAY.
THAT'S WHAT SHE WANTS.
Asuna: DOCTOR, CAN SHE USE
THE MEDICUBOID NOW?
Dr. Kurahashi:
BUT, WELL, WOULDN'T SHE WANT
TO SPEND HER LAST MOMENTS HERE?
Asuna: NO. SHE WANTS
TO GO BACK ONE LAST TIME.
PLEASE, DOCTOR, LET HER USE
THE MEDICUBOID AGAIN.
Dr. Kurahashi: MM.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE
ABOUT A MINUTE TO BOOT UP.
THEN WHAT?
I'M GOING NEXT DOOR
TO LOG IN WITH THE AMUSPHERE.
WAIT FOR ME, YUUKI. I'M COMING.
(WIND BLOWING)
Yuuki: THANKS, ASUNA.
I'M GLAD I GOT TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
'CAUSE I GOT SOMETHIN' FOR YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I ALMOST FORGOT ABOUT IT.
Asuna: REALLY? WHAT IS IT
YOU WANTED TO GIVE ME?
Yuuki: OH, UM,
I STILL GOTTA MAKE IT.
HANG ON A SEC.
(YELLING)
Asuna: YUUKI!
Yuuki: THAT'S WEIRD.
I FEEL SO WEAK ALL OF A SUDDEN.
I'M NOT IN ANY PAIN
OR ANYTHING, THOUGH.
Asuna: IT'S OKAY. YOU'RE JUST
A LITTLE TIRED, IS ALL.
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER IF YOU REST.
Yuuki: YEAH, MAYBE.
LISTEN, ASUNA, TAKE THIS.
IT'S MY ORIGINAL SWORD SKILL.
Asuna: NO, YUUKI, I COULDN'T.
Yuuki: OH, COME ON.
I WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
OPEN THE WINDOW.
(SIGHS)
I GAVE IT A COOL NAME,
MOTHER'S ROSARIO.
I‐IT'LL KEEP YOU SAFE
WHEN YOU NEED IT.
Asuna: THANK YOU, YUUKI.
I PROMISE
I'LL TAKE GOOD CARE OF IT,
AND SOMEDAY,
WHEN I LEAVE THIS WORLD,
I'LL MAKE SURE TO PASS IT ON
TO SOMEONE BEFORE I GO.
YOUR SWORD'LL LIVE ON
UNTIL THE END OF TIME.
Yuuki: THANK YOU.
(WIND BLOWING)
AWW, GUYS. COME ON.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
YOU PROMISED, NO GOOD‐BYES.
Jun: NAH, YOU GOT IT WRONG.
WE'RE ALL HERE TO CHEER YOU UP.
WHEN YOU GET TO THE OTHER SIDE,
WAIT FOR US, OKAY.
WE WON'T TAKE TOO LONG, PROMISE.
Yuuki: WHAT'RE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IF YOU GET THERE TOO SOON,
I'LL BE PISSED.
Nori: TSK, TSK!
YOU KNOW THE DEAL.
YOU'RE HOPELESS WITHOUT US,
SO DON'T EVEN TRY TO ARGUE!
JUST SIT TIGHT, AND WAIT FOR‐‐
FOR US.
Siune: PLEASE, NORI, DON'T CRY.
WE PROMISED WE'D BE STRONG.
Yuuki: I GIVE UP. YOU WIN.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU.
BUT TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU GOT IT?
All: Mm‐hmm.
Players: (GASPING)
Yuuki: WHOA.
LOOK AT ALL THOSE FAIRIES.
Asuna: I'M SORRY.
I HAD TO LET THEM KNOW.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT MAD AT ME.
Yuuki: ARE YOU KIDDING?
WHY WOULD I BE MAD?
THERE'S SO MANY OF 'EM.
IT'S LIKE A DREAM.
WHY ARE THEY HERE?
Asuna: BECAUSE OF YOU.
YOU'RE THE STRONGEST,
MOST POWERFUL SWORDSWOMAN
THIS WORLD'S EVER SEEN.
THERE WILL NEVER BE
ANYONE ELSE LIKE YOU AGAIN.
WE CAN'T LET YOU GO
WITHOUT SAYING GOOD‐BYE.
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
WE'RE ALL PRAYING FOR YOU,
THAT YOUR NEXT JOURNEY
WILL BE TO A PLACE
AS WONDERFUL AS THIS.
Yuuki: I'M HAPPY.
I'M SO HAPPY.
YOU KNOW, THIS WHOLE TIME,
I THOUGHT IF I WAS BORN TO DIE,
WHAT THE HECK WAS THE POINT
OF ME EVEN BEING BORN?
I NEVER MADE ANYTHING
OR GAVE ANYTHING TO ANYONE.
ALL I DID WAS WASTE DRUGS
AND HOG THAT MACHINE
AND CAUSE TROUBLE FOR EVERYONE.
IF ALL I GET TO DO IS SUFFER
AND DISAPPEAR IN THE END,
IT'D BE BETTER
TO JUST DISAPPEAR RIGHT NOW.
I USED TO ALWAYS THINK,
WHY AM I ALIVE?
WHY'D I STICK AROUND
FOR THIS LONG?
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
I THINK I KNOW WHY NOW.
I MIGHT NOT HAVE DONE MUCH,
BUT I'M GLAD I GOT TO LIVE,
'CAUSE AFTER EVERYTHING,
THESE LAST FEW MOMENTS,
THEY'RE THE BEST EVER.
I'M SURROUNDED
BY ALL MY FRIENDS,
AND I GOT TO END MY JOURNEY
IN THE ARMS OF SOMEONE I LOVE.
Asuna: YUUKI, I PROMISE,
I WILL SEE YOU AGAIN SOMEDAY,
IN SOME OTHER PLACE,
SOME OTHER WORLD.
I DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT I'LL FIND YOU,
AND THEN WE CAN SIT AND TALK,
AND YOU COULD TELL ME
WHERE YOU'VE BEEN.
Yuuki, thinking: I GAVE
THIS LIFE EVERYTHING I HAD.
I WAS ALIVE.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
Yuuki: I NEVER MADE ANYTHING
OR GAVE ANYTHING TO ANYONE.
Asuna: YOU GAVE ME SOMETHING.
YOU CARVED IT
DEEP INTO MY HEART,
AND IT'LL ALWAYS BE THERE.
Woman: HELLO, ASUNA.
HOW ARE YOU?
Asuna: WAIT.
IS THAT YOU, SIUNE?
Siune: YES, IN THE FLESH.
IT'S NICE TO FINALLY
MEET YOU IN THE REAL WORLD.
I'M SHI‐EUN AN.
Asuna: OH!
I‐IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU, TOO.
I'M ASUNA YUUKI.
LIKE MEETING
FOR THE FIRST TIME, HUH?
Both: (LAUGH)
‐ Asuna: BUT‐‐
‐ Siune: NO, IT'S OKAY.
JUST THIS MONTH, I GOT
THE ALL‐CLEAR FROM MY DOCTOR
AND WAS DISCHARGED
FROM THE HOSPITAL.
Asuna: THEN,
YOU'RE DOING BETTER?
Siune: YES.
THE TYPE OF DISEASE I HAVE
IS CALLED
ACUTE LYMPHOCYTIC LEUKEMIA,
AND IT WAS ABOUT THREE YEARS AGO
WHEN I DEVELOPED IT.
THE SIDE EFFECTS FROM
THE MEDICINE WERE SO HORRIBLE,
I WANTED TO DIE
RATHER THAN KEEP SUFFERING,
BUT WHENEVER I SAW YUUKI,
I THOUGHT, "HERE'S THIS KID,
AND SHE'S HANDLING HER SITUATION
BETTER THAN I'M HANDLING MINE."
AROUND FEBRUARY,
THEY STARTED CUTTING BACK
ON THE MEDS I WAS ON.
I THOUGHT, "THIS IS IT,"
AND I BRACED MYSELF FOR THE END.
AND THEN A WEEK AGO,
THE DAY AFTER YUUKI DIED,
MY DOCTOR CAME IN AND SAID,
"CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'RE IN COMPLETE REMISSION."
NEXT THING I KNEW,
I WAS BEING DISCHARGED.
I BARELY HAD A CHANCE
TO PROCESS THE NEWS.
AND THE TRUTH IS,
IT STILL HASN'T SUNK IN YET.
IT'S LIKE I SHOULD FEEL AWFUL.
IT DOESN'T SEEM FAIR
THAT I'M STILL HERE
AND YUUKI'S WAITING.
YUUKI AND RAN,
CLOVIS AND MERIDA,
WE PROMISED
WE'D STICK TOGETHER FOREVER,
AND I‐I'M HERE, AND‐‐
Asuna: SHI‐EUN.
YOU KNOW,
OUR LIVES ARE LIKE VESSELS,
AND WE CARRY THE TEACHINGS
OF THE ONES
WHO'VE PASSED IN THEM.
FOR THE LONGEST TIME,
I WAS SO SCARED,
SCARED OF TELLING SOMEONE
HOW I REALLY FELT
AND SCARED OF FINDING OUT
HOW THEY FELT.
BUT I LEARNED FROM YUUKI
THAT THAT WAS NO WAY
FOR ME TO LIVE.
IF I DIDN'T EVEN
TRY TO REACH OUT,
NOTHING WOULD EVER CHANGE.
SHE TAUGHT ME HOW TO BE STRONG,
AND I WANT TO SHARE THAT
WITH OTHERS.
AS LONG AS I'M ALIVE,
I'LL PASS ON WHAT I LEARNED
FROM HER TO EVERYONE I MEET,
AND THEN SOMEDAY,
WHEN I SEE HER AGAIN,
I WANT TO TELL HER ABOUT
ALL THE PEOPLE SHE'S HELPED.
THAT'S HOW I'LL PAY HER BACK.
Siune: THANK YOU, ASUNA.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALL SO GRATEFUL
FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
I'D BEEN SO WORRIED ABOUT YUUKI.
SHE WAS CARRYING A HEAVY BURDEN
ON THOSE
LITTLE SHOULDERS OF HERS,
BUT THEN YOU SHOWED UP,
AND SOMETHING IN HER CHANGED.
WHEN YOU WERE TOGETHER,
YUUKI SEEMED LIKE SHE WAS
REALLY HAVING FUN.
SHE WAS LIKE A FORGETFUL BIRD
WHO REMEMBERED HOW TO FLY,
AND SHE FLEW UP AND UP,
AND NOW SHE'S OUT OF OUR REACH.
ANYWAY, JUN'S ALSO DOING GREAT.
THE MEDICATION HE'S ON
SEEMS TO BE WORKING.
IT'S LIKE‐‐I DON'T KNOW.
TO ME, IT FEELS LIKE YUUKI'S
TELLING ALL OF US
IT'S STILL TOO SOON TO JOIN HER.
I GUESS THAT MEANS
IT'S GOING TO BE A WHILE YET
BEFORE THE SLEEPING KNIGHTS
GET BACK TOGETHER.
Asuna: JUST REMEMBER, NEXT TIME,
YOU'RE TAKING ME IN AS A MEMBER,
AND I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ANY ARGUMENTS.
Both: (LAUGH)
Kirito: HEY.
I HOPE WE'RE
NOT INTERRUPTING ANYTHING.
Asuna: NO. BUT WAIT.
DO YOU GUYS KNOW EACH OTHER?
Kirito: SORT OF.
HE'S TRYING TO STEAL MY IDEAS
ABOUT THAT COMMUNICATIONS POD
I MADE.
Dr. Kurahashi: NO, HE'S LYING.
I'M INTERESTED
IN ITS POSSIBILITIES
IN FULL‐DIVE MEDICAL TECH,
SO WE'VE BEEN
E‐MAILING BACK AND FORTH.
Asuna: THAT'S GREAT
FOR BOTH OF YOU.
WHAT ABOUT THE MEDICUBOID?
ARE YOU GOING TO PHASE IT OUT,
OR WERE THE TRIALS SUCCESSFUL?
Dr. Kurahashi: GLAD YOU ASKED.
THEY WERE EXTREMELY SUCCESSFUL,
AND NOW WE HAVE ENOUGH DATA
TO PROCEED TO THE NEXT PHASE.
SOON, PATIENTS ALL OVER
THE COUNTRY WILL HAVE‐‐
I AM SO SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DIDN'T SAY THIS FIRST.
MS. AN, CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR RECOVERY.
I KNOW YUUKI WOULD BE THRILLED
AT THE NEWS, TOO.
Siune: THANK YOU FOR SAYING SO,
AND CONGRATULATIONS
ON THE TRIALS.
IT'S GOOD TO KNOW
WHAT YOU LEARNED FROM YUUKI
WILL BE USED TO HELP OTHERS.
THAT MAKES ME HAPPY.
Dr. Kurahashi: ME, TOO.
YUUKI WAS THE FIRST PERSON
TO TEST THE MEDICUBOID,
AND HER NAME
WILL ALWAYS BE REMEMBERED.
IF SHE WERE HERE,
SHE'D GET AN AWARD FOR HER HELP,
ALONG WITH THE BENEFACTOR
WHO MADE IT ALL POSSIBLE.
Siune: KNOWING YUUKI,
SHE WOULDN'T BE TOO THRILLED
AT GETTING AN AWARD.
SHE'D SAY,
"WHAT'S THE POINT IN HAVING IT
IF I CAN'T EAT IT?"
All: (LAUGH)
Asuna: UM, DOCTOR,
YOU JUST MENTIONED
THE MEDICUBOID
HAD SOME KIND OF BENEFACTOR?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THE GOVERNMENT
WAS PAYING FOR IT.
Dr. Kurahashi:
OH, WELL, YES, THEY ARE,
BUT THE INITIAL DESIGNS
WERE GIVEN TO US FOR FREE
FROM SOMEONE ELSE.
IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
I THINK HER NAME
WAS DR. RINKO KOUJIRO.
Kirito: (GASPS)
Asuna: W‐WHAT'S WRONG, KIRITO?
Kirito: I‐‐I KNOW HER
Asuna: HOW?
Kirito: I MET HER ONCE.
YEAH, IN FACT,
SHE WAS TAKING CARE
OF HEATHCLIFF'S BODY
WHILE HE WAS DIVING.
SHE WAS HIS HEAD RESEARCHER.
SHE HELPED HIM DEVELOP
FULL‐DIVE TECHNOLOGY.
YOU SEE?
THE MEDICUBOID'S DESIGN,
YOU KNOW WHO INVENTED IT?
Asuna: NO WAY.
IT WAS KAYABA.
Agil: NEED ANY HELP
UNPACKING ALL THIS STUFF?
Leafa: SURE,
BUT ONLY IF YOU'RE NOT BUSY.
Klein: SERIOUSLY,
AIN'T SHE CUTE?
‐ Lisbeth: UH...
‐ Silica: UH...
Leafa: I GOT YOU A LITTLE GIFT.
Sinon: NO WAY.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE.
‐ Leafa: HEY...
‐ Klein: YOU GUYS SUCK.
Asuna: ARE YOU HAVING FUN
HANGING OUT HERE WITH EVERYONE?
Yui: YES!
AND THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS
ARE PRETTY.
Kirito: YEAH, IT'S TOO BAD
THEY'RE ALMOST GONE.
Asuna: OH, PLEASE,
THERE'S PLENTY LEFT,
YOU SPOILSPORT.
ANYWAY, WE'RE HERE WITH YUI.
THAT'S THE IMPORTANT THING.
Kirito: I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
WE MADE IT HAPPEN THAT FAST.
Yui: THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR THIS, DADDY.
Asuna: YEAH, KIRITO, THANK YOU.
Kirito: NAH, IF YOU WANT
TO THANK SOMEONE,
THANK YUUKI
FOR HELPING ME DEVELOP IT.
(WIND GUSTS)
Yui: WOW!
Kirito: THE REAL WORLD
AND THE VIRTUAL,
I THOUGHT THE CLOSER
THEY CAME TOGETHER,
THE BETTER THE FUTURE WOULD BE.
Asuna: HM?
Kirito: IT'S LIKE
THE MORE THE LINES
BETWEEN THESE WORLDS BLUR,
THE MORE EVERYONE
GETS SUCKED INTO ITS DARKNESS.
Asuna: YEAH, BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN HELPED BY IT, TOO.
Kirito: IF ANYTHING,
I WISH I KNEW
WHAT KAYABA'S MASTER PLAN WAS.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S OUR JOB
AS SURVIVORS OF "S. A. O."
TO FIND OUT.
Asuna: I THINK
YOU'RE OVERTHINKING THINGS.
Kirito: YEAH, I GUESS.
STILL, I WANNA FIND OUT
MORE THAN EVER NOW.
EVEN AFTER
EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED,
MY CURIOSITY'S GOT ME HOOKED.
ALTHOUGH, A PART OF ME
THINKS I'M BEING PLAYED HERE.
THAT'S KIND OF ANNOYING.
WHATEVER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GONNA HAPPEN TOMORROW.
ALL I KNOW IS
I WANNA BE WITH YOU FOREVER,
AND I WANT YOU TO BE WITH ME.
Asuna: (LAUGHS)
I'LL STICK BY YOU,
EVEN IF YOU MOVE
HALFWAY ACROSS THE PLANET.
Kirito: WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT MOVING?
Yui: DON'T FORGET
TO TAKE ME ALONG.
Lisbeth: HEY, LOVEBIRDS!
QUIT MAKIN' OUT!
WE WANNA TAKE A PHOTO!
‐ Klein: GET OVER HERE, GUYS!
‐ Lisbeth: TODAY, GUYS!
‐ Agil: HURRY UP!
‐ Klein: MOVE IT, DUDE!
Kirito: WELL, SHALL WE?
Asuna: MM‐HMM.
Yui: OKAY, DADDY.