Yui: PUNCHES INCOMING,
TWO IN A ROW!
All: (GASP)
Leafa: (GASPS)
Klein: (YELLS)
Thrmyr: (GROANS)
Yui: HIS ICE BREATH IS NEXT!
COMING UP IN THREE,
TWO, ONE, NOW!
Thrmyr: (SCREAMING)
Kirito: NOW IT'S OUR TURN!
All: (YELL)
Leafa: (YELLS)
Thrmyr: (YELLS)
Kirito: ATTACK PATTERN'S
CHANGING! STAY SHARP!
Leafa: OH, MY GOD. KAZUTO!
THERE'S ONLY
THREE CLEAR SPOTS LEFT.
CAN'T YOU USE
THAT SKILL CONNECTOR THINGIE
YOU USED BEFORE?
Kirito: HE'S STILL GOT
TWO BARS LEFT ON HIS H. P. GAUGE.
SKILL CONNECT
WON'T EVEN PUT A DENT IN IT.
Thrmyr: (INHALES)
Kirito: WATCH OUT!
ICE BREATH COMING UP!
Leafa: OH, NO. THE BUFF!
KAZUTO, WA‐‐
Thrmyr: (GRUNTS)
Players: (GROAN)
Asuna: (GASPS)
GET OUT OF THERE!
Thrmyr: (GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
Kirito: SINON,
KEEP HIM BUSY FOR A FEW!
Thrmyr: EH?
Freyja: SWORDSMAN,
IF WE CONTINUE
THIS COURSE OF ACTION,
WE WILL NOT DEFEAT THRMYR.
THERE IS BUT ONE HOPE NOW.
SOMEWHERE IN THIS ROOM,
HIDDEN IN THE PLUNDER,
YOU WILL FIND
THE TREASURE OF MY PEOPLE.
Kirito: I'M ON IT.
TELL ME WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE,
AND I'LL GRAB IT.
Freyja: IT IS ABOUT YEA BIG.
IT IS A HAMMER MADE OF GOLD.
Kirito: WAIT. IT'S A HAMMER?
(GROANS)
Leafa: (GASPS) HEY, KAZUTO,
YOU CAN FIND IT
USING A LIGHTNING SKILL.
Kirito: LIGHTNING? REALLY?
Both: (GASP)
Kirito: THERE IT IS.
(GRUNTING)
FREYJA, CATCH!
Freyja: (GASPS)
IT FLOWS INTO ME.
Kirito: HUH?
Klein: F‐FREYJA?
Freyja: THROUGH ME,
IT OVERFLOWS.
(SCREAMING)
Kirito: FREYJA? UH...
Man: (GRUNTS)
Asuna and Sinon: (GASPING)
Klein: SHE'S A...
Klein and Kirito:
A FRIGGING DUDE?!
Kirito: OH, HE'S THOR,
THE GOD OF THUNDER.
Thor: (ROARS)
Thrmyr: HMM?
Thor: YOU DESPICABLE GIANT,
YOUR TREACHERY AND DECEIT
HAS COME TO AN END,
AND NOW YOU SHALL PAY
FOR STEALING MJOLNIR!
Thrmyr: I SHALL MAKE YOU PAY
FOR DECEIVING ME,
YOU MISERABLE EXCUSE OF A GOD.
I SHALL RIP THAT BEARD
FROM YOUR FACE
AND SEND YOUR BODY
BACK TO ASGARD!
Sinon: THOR'S PULLING AGGRO
FROM THRMYR.
LET'S ATTACK WHILE WE CAN.
Kirito: HERE WE GO, GUYS!
HIT HIM HARD!
DON'T HOLD BACK!
USE ALL YOUR SWORD SKILLS!
Klein: FREYJA!
YAAH!
Thrmyr: (YELLS)
(GROANS)
Kirito: THIS IS IT!
Thrmyr: (SCREAMS)
Thor: RETURN TO YOUR ABYSS,
KING OF THE GIANTS!
Thrmyr: (GROANS)
(LAUGHS)
REVEL IN YOUR VICTORY, INSECTS,
BUT TAKE HEED.
IF YOU PUT YOUR FAITH
IN THE DOGS OF AESIR...
Thor: YOU HAVE MY GRATITUDE,
BRAVE FAERIE WARRIORS.
THANKS TO YOU,
MY TREASURE HAS BEEN RETURNED
AND MY DISGRACE AVENGED.
NOW THEN, I MUST REWARD YOU.
THAT IS MJOLNIR,
THE LIGHTNING HAMMER.
USE IT IN NOBLE BATTLES.
FAREWELL, MY CHAMPIONS.
Leafa: (CHUCKLES)
Kirito: CONGRATS, PAL.
YOU'VE GOT A LEGENDARY WEAPON.
Klein: YEAH, BUT IT'S A HAMMER.
I DON'T GOT NO HAMMER SKILLS.
(WHIMPERS)
‐ (CASTLE RUMBLING)
‐ EH?
All: (YELLING)
Sinon: THE‐‐THE ROOM'S MOVING.
WAIT. IS IT FLOATING?
Leafa: HEY, KAZUTO,
I DON'T THINK THIS QUEST
IS OVER YET.
Kirito: HUH?
Urd: GOOD FAERIES,
INFILTRATE THRYMHEIM,
REMOVE EXCALIBUR
FROM ITS PLINTH,
AND SAVE MY REALM.
Leafa: LOOK AT THE MEDALLION.
IT'S ALL BLACK
EXCEPT FOR THAT ONE CLEAR SPOT.
Yui: DADDY,
A STAIRWAY LEADING DOWN
HAS JUST APPEARED
BEHIND THE THRONE.
Kirito: SERIOUSLY?
LET'S GO.
Kirito: SYSTEM COMMAND,
GENERATE OBJECT!
I.D., EXCALIBUR!
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
(GRUNTING)
Asuna: YOU GOT IT, KIRITO!
Lisbeth: COME ON! PULL HARDER!
Sinon: PUT YOUR BACK INTO IT!
Yui: DON'T GIVE UP, DADDY!
Silica: YOU CAN DO IT!
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT!
‐ Pina: (SQUAWKS)
‐ Klein: GO! KEEP PULLING!
Kirito: (GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
‐ Klein: AW, CRAP.
‐ Pina: (SQUAWKS)
Klein: IT'S BREAKING UP.
Yui: DADDY,
THRYMHEIM IS COLLAPSING.
WE HAVE TO LEAVE HERE NOW.
Kirito: I KNOW. I KNOW.
Klein: HEH. ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S UP TO ME
TO SAVE THE DAY.
TIME FOR SOME OLYMPIC‐GRADE
HIGH JUMPING.
OW!
All: (YELLING)
Kirito: WE'RE SO SCREWED.
LEAFA, HOW MUCH TIME WE GOT?
Leafa: (GASPS) WE MADE IT.
THANK GOD. WE MADE IT!
Kirito: YEAH.
(INTERFACE BEEPING)
(THINKING) LOOKS LIKE
I CAN'T CLAIM EXCALIBUR
UNLESS THE QUEST IS CLEARED.
(GROANS)
Leafa: (GASPS)
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
Kirito: HUH?
Leafa: (GASPS)
THERE IT IS AGAIN.
Tonky: (BELLOWING)
Leafa: TONKY!
Asuna: WE'RE SAVED!
Klein: HURRY, GUYS.
HOP ON HIS BACK.
Kirito:
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
Klein: YEAH, I KNOW!
(SIGHS)
WISH IT WASN'T SO HIGH UP.
Kirito: GO ON. JUMP!
Klein: (YELLS)
HUH?
Tonky: (BELLOWS)
Klein: HEY, TONKY.
THANKS FOR SAVING MY ASS.
Kirito: (THINKING) I GUESS
YOU'RE STILL TOO HEAVY FOR ME.
Yui: DADDY?
Kirito: SERIOUSLY,
STUPID CARDINAL SYSTEM.
Sinon: THAT'S ABOUT 200 METERS.
All: HUH?
Klein: UH...
Kirito: UH...
Sinon: ECKU, SKEATA, AFTOL, ALE.
Kirito: YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
Sinon: WHOA. HEAVY.
Players: S‐S‐S...
SINON, THAT WAS AWESOME!
Sinon: DON'T LOOK
AT ME LIKE THAT.
YOU CAN HAVE IT. HERE.
Kirito: THANKS.
YOU'RE THE BEST. UH...
Sinon: I'LL GIVE IT TO YOU,
BUT WITH ONE CONDITION.
YOU GOTTA PROMISE ME...
EVERY TIME YOU DRAW IT,
YOU HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT ME, OKAY?
Kirito: UH...
Girls: (GROANING)
Klein: WELL, WELL,
THE CHICK MAGNET'S
GOT ANOTHER GIRL‐‐
UHH!
Kirito: (CLEARS THROAT)
YOU GOT IT.
I'LL THINK ABOUT YOU
EVERY TIME I DRAW IT.
THANKS A LOT.
Sinon: YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME.
(CHUCKLES)
Tonky: (BELLOWS)
Lisbeth: MAN, THIS SUCKS.
WE ONLY GOT TO DO
ONE QUEST IN IT,
AND NOW IT'S GONE FOR GOOD.
Silica: I KNOW.
IT SEEMS LIKE SUCH A WASTE.
All: (GASP)
Asuna: LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S SPROUTING.
Pina: (SQUAWKS)
Silica: SO WARM.
Tonky: (BELLOWS)
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: HE'S HAPPY.
Jelly‐phants: (BELLOWING)
Tonky: (BELLOWS)
Leafa: I'M HAPPY, TOO.
ISN'T THIS GREAT, TONKY?
LOOK, ALL YOUR FRIENDS
HAVE COME TO SAY HI.
YOU SEE 'EM?
THEY'RE ALL WAVING.
YOU'RE A POPULAR GUY.
(CHIMES RINGING)
Players: EH?
Urd: YOU REMOVED EXCALIBUR
FROM ITS PLINTH.
THE QUEST HAS BEEN COMPLETED.
NOW THAT THE SWORD WHICH SLICES
WOOD AND IRON IS SECURE,
JOTUNHEIM CAN RETURN
TO ITS FORMER GLORY.
IT IS ALL THANKS TO YOU
AND YOUR BRAVERY.
MY YOUNGER SISTERS
WOULD ALSO LIKE TO EXPRESS
THEIR GRATITUDE TOWARDS YOU.
Verdandi: MY NAME IS VERDANDI.
THANK YOU,
O BRAVE FAERIE WARRIORS.
TO THINK I CAN GAZE
UPON A GREEN JOTUNHEIM AGAIN,
OH, IT'S LIKE A DREAM.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
Klein: (GULPS)
Skuld: AND MY NAME IS SKULD.
YOU HAVE MY THANKS AND RESPECT.
(BLOWS)
Urd: MY GIFT TO YOU
SHALL BE THE HOLY SWORD.
Kirito: YES.
Sisters: THANK YOU,
NOBLE FAERIES,
UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN.
Kirito: WE FINALLY CLEARED IT.
Klein: UM, 'SCUSE ME,
LADY SKULD,
CAN I GET YOUR NUMBER?!
‐ Players: (GASP)
‐ Pina: (SQUAWKS)
Skuld: (GIGGLES)
Lisbeth: HEH HEH.
RIGHT NOW, I RESPECT YOU
MORE THAN EVER, KLEIN.
YOU CAN BE A DORK,
BUT YOU GOT HEART.
Kirito: HOW'S THAT, YUI?
Yui: I CAN SEE PERFECTLY, DADDY,
AND I CAN HEAR, TOO.
Sinon: COOL, BUT WHAT IS IT?
Kirito: I'M TURNING
REAL‐TIME FOOTAGE OF THE CAFE
INTO MOCK‐3D IMAGES.
OKAY, TRY MOVING,
BUT TAKE IT SLOW.
Yui: OKAY.
Kirito: IF IT'S WORKING RIGHT,
YUI SHOULD FEEL LIKE SHE'S
FLYING AROUND THE ROOM.
Yui: (GIGGLES)
Sinon: I GET IT.
THAT CAMERA AND ITS MIC
ARE ACTING
LIKE YUI'S EYES AND EARS.
GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU,
THAT'S PRETTY CLEVER.
Leafa: KAZUTO'S TAKING
A CLASS CALLED MECHO‐‐
MECHA‐SOMETHING.
Kirito: IT'S MECHATRONICS.
Leafa: LIKE I WAS SAYING,
HE'S TAKING
THIS MECHA‐THING CLASS.
HE HAS TO DO A PROJECT,
SO HE CAME UP WITH THIS IDEA.
BUT IF YOU ASK ME,
HE'S JUST DOING IT FOR YUI.
Yui: YOU'RE SPOILING ME, DADDY.
‐ Kirito: HMM?
‐ Leafa: EH?
All: (LAUGHING)
["NO MORE TIME MACHINE"
BY LiSA PLAYING IN JAPANESE]
Players: (CHATTING)
Kirito: NICE JOB, GUYS.
WE GOT THE HOLY SWORD EXCALIBUR
AND MJOLNIR,
THE LIGHTNING HAMMER.
CONGRATS.
TO 2025.
TO US.
All: TO US!
Sinon: HEY, I WAS WONDERING,
WHY DID THEY CALL IT
EXCALIBUR IN THE GAME?
Kirito: HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WHY?
Sinon: WELL, USUALLY
IN THE FANTASY BOOKS
AND COMICS I'VE READ,
IT'S ALWAYS CALLED CALIBURN,
NOT EXCALIBUR.
Kirito: OH. I DON'T KNOW.
Leafa: NO WAY.
YOU DON'T SEEM LIKE SOMEONE
WHO'D BE A FAN OF FANTASY BOOKS.
Sinon: (CHUCKLES)
WHEN I WAS IN MIDDLE SCHOOL,
I PRETTY MUCH LIVED
AT THE LIBRARY.
I SPENT ALL MY TIME THERE
READING BOOKS ABOUT KING ARTHUR.
EVERY ONE OF 'EM
REFERRED TO IT AS CALIBURN.
Asuna: ACTUALLY,
DIDN'T THE SWORD
GO BY A LOT OF DIFFERENT NAMES
IN MOST OF THOSE LEGENDS?
Sinon: DEPENDING ON
WHICH CELTIC LANGUAGE,
BUT THE WORD CALIBER IS COOL,
'CAUSE IT'S WHAT YOU CALL
THE DIAMETER OF A GUN BARREL
AND IT'S ALSO HOW YOU DESCRIBE
THE QUALITY
OF A PERSON'S CHARACTER.
Leafa:
THANKS FOR THE LESSON, TEACH.
Sinon: SORRY IF I
GOT CARRIED AWAY THERE.
Lisbeth: SO BASICALLY
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
IS WHOEVER OWNS EXCALIBUR
HAS TO BE SOMEONE
WHO'S AN EXCEPTIONAL PERSON.
Silica: HUH? WHO IS?
YOU MEAN KIRITO?
Lisbeth: YEAH, OF COURSE. DUH.
IN FACT, HE'S SO EXCEPTIONAL,
HE WOULDN'T THINK TWICE
ABOUT PAYING FOR DINNER
WITH SOME OF THAT CRAZY MONEY
HE MADE, RIGHT?
Kirito: YEAH. I WAS SAVING IT
FOR A SURPRISE,
BUT, YEAH, TOTALLY.
THIS DINNER'S ON ME.
Girls: (LAUGH)
‐ THANK YOU, KIRITO.
‐ OH, THANKS, KIRITO.
Sinon: IT'S FREE?
Klein: YEAH. START POURING
THE TOP‐SHELF STUFF.
WE'RE GONNA EAT
TILL YOU'RE BROKE, DUDE.
Players: (CHATTING)
(CAMERA CLICKS)