Asuna: (GASPS)
Siune: ASUNA.
Asuna: (GASPS) SIUNE.
PLEASE, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO YUUKI?
IT'S BEEN THREE DAYS,
AND SHE HASN'T LOGGED BACK IN.
Siune: IT'S NOT JUST YOU.
NONE OF US HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO CONTACT HER EITHER.
ASUNA, I HATE TO SAY THIS,
BUT I DON'T THINK
SHE WANTS TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I THINK SHE'S DOING IT
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
Asuna: (GASPS) BUT WHY?
I HAD A FEELING
SOMETHING WASN'T RIGHT.
I COULD TELL
EVERYONE IN THE GROUP
WAS AVOIDING
GETTING TOO CLOSE TO ME.
THE LAST THING I WANT
IS TO UPSET ANYONE
OR BE A NUISANCE.
BUT STILL, I DON'T SEE HOW ANY
OF THIS COULD BE FOR MY SAKE!
Siune: YOU'RE NOT A NUISANCE!
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
BELIEVE ME WHEN I SAY
WE'RE ALL TRULY HAPPY
TO HAVE MET YOU.
WE GOT TO HAVE
ONE LAST AMAZING MEMORY
OF OUR TIME TOGETHER HERE,
AND IT'S ALL THANKS TO YOU.
AND YUUKI,
I KNOW SHE'S GRATEFUL, TOO,
BUT PLEASE,
FORGET YOU EVER MET US.
IT REALLY IS THE BEST THING
FOR YOU AND FOR YUUKI.
Asuna: I CAN'T EVER SEE
ANY OF YOU AGAIN?
I THOUGHT
AFTER THE GUILD WAS GONE,
I THOUGHT WE COULD AT LEAST
KEEP ON BEING FRIENDS,
BUT THIS WHOLE TIME,
I WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO THOUGHT THAT?
Siune: I'M SORRY.
Asuna: NO, WAIT!
Lisbeth: ASUNA!
MORNING.
Silica: MORNING, ASUNA.
Asuna: GOOD MORNING.
Lisbeth: AH,
WE FINALLY CAUGHT YOU.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE HERE,
SO YOU GONNA TELL US
WHAT THAT MESSAGE WAS ABOUT?
Silica: IS IT TRUE?
LIZ SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT YOU JOINING A GUILD.
‐ Asuna: (GASPS)
‐ Lisbeth: COME ON.
COME ON, TELL US. ARE THEY COOL?
Asuna: WELL, IT'S LIKE‐‐
(RINGTONE CHIMING)
OH, HANG ON A SEC.
HUH?
Kirito: ALL RIGHT, HOW'S THAT?
CAN YOU SEE MY FACE OKAY?
Yui: I SEE YOU,
BUT YOU'RE A LITTLE BLURRY.
Kirito: HMM.
IT'S THE AUTOFOCUS AGAIN.
IT'S GOTTA BE THAT.
GIVE ME A SEC, YUI.
Yui: OKAY, DADDY.
Kirito: HEY.
THIS ZEKKEN,
YOU STILL WANT TO SEE HER?
Asuna: (GASPS)
MM‐HMM.
Kirito: EVEN AFTER THEY SAY
IT'S BETTER YOU DIDN'T,
YOU STILL DO?
Asuna: MM‐HMM.
I DON'T CARE WHAT THEY SAY.
ALL I WANT IS TO TALK
TO YUUKI ONE LAST TIME.
I CAN'T LEAVE IT LIKE THIS.
Kirito: OKAY.
I THINK I MIGHT HAVE FOUND
WHERE SHE'S AT.
I'M NOT SURE,
BUT IT'S THE BEST I GOT.
Asuna: WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
SHE'D BE HERE?
Kirito: THAT PLACE HAS
A MEDICUBOID.
THEY'RE THE ONLY ONES DOING
THE CLINICAL TRIALS FOR IT.
Asuna: MEDICUBOID?
EXCUSE ME.
Receptionist: MAY I HELP YOU?
Asuna: YES.
I, UM‐‐I THINK
I'M LOOKING FOR A PATIENT.
Receptionist: UH...
Asuna: WELL, SHE'S ABOUT
15 YEARS OLD OR SO.
I THINK HER NAME MIGHT BE YUUKI,
BUT I'M NOT SURE.
Receptionist:
I NEED A NAME AT LEAST.
Asuna: OH. UM, WELL, I THINK
SHE MIGHT BE THE PATIENT
WHO'S TESTING
THAT MEDICUBOID THING.
Second receptionist:
PARDON ME, MISS.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
Asuna: UH, OH, SORRY.
MY NAME IS ASUNA YUUKI.
Second receptionist: (GASPS)
PLEASE HAVE A SEAT.
I'LL GET SOMEONE RIGHT AWAY.
Asuna: UM, SURE.
(FOOTSTEPS)
Doctor: HI. SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I HOPE YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN WAITING LONG.
Asuna: NO, NOT AT ALL.
Doctor: THAT'S GOOD.
THEY TOLD ME YOU'RE ASUNA YUUKI.
Asuna: YES.
Doctor: GREAT.
I'M DR. KURAHASHI.
I'M YUUKI KONNO'S
PRIMARY PHYSICIAN.
Asuna: YUUKI KONNO.
Dr. Kurahashi: YOU KNOW,
I'M SURPRISED YOU EVEN FOUND US.
Asuna: WHY?
Dr. Kurahashi: OH,
WELL, WE KEEP A LOW PROFILE.
THAT SAID, YUUKI WARNED ME
SOMEONE CALLED ASUNA
MIGHT TRY AND PAY HER A VISIT
AT SOME POINT.
Asuna: SHE WARNED YOU?
Dr. Kurahashi: UH‐HUH.
SHE ALSO SAID
SHE DIDN'T TELL YOU
WHERE SHE WAS,
SO I SAID,
"DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT."
SHE'S NOT GONNA FIND YOU HERE."
WHEN RECEPTION TOLD ME
YOU WERE IN THE LOBBY,
I WAS SHOCKED.
Asuna: DOCTOR, HAS YUUKI
TOLD YOU ANYTHING ELSE
ABOUT ME OR HOW WE MET?
Dr. Kurahashi: I'LL SAY SHE HAS.
YOU'RE PRETTY MUCH
THE ONLY PERSON SHE TALKS ABOUT.
ALTHOUGH, IT SEEMS
WHENEVER YUUKI DOES MENTION YOU,
SHE ALWAYS ENDS UP IN TEARS.
Asuna: (GASPS)
Dr. Kurahashi: SHE'S ALWAYS
BEEN A BRAVE GIRL
AND NEVER FELT SORRY
FOR HERSELF.
SHE WANTS TO SEE YOU,
BUT SHE CAN'T BRING HERSELF
TO DO IT.
Asuna: YES, I KNOW,
AND I STILL CAN'T WRAP
MY HEAD AROUND IT.
A FRIEND OF HERS TOLD ME IN‐GAME
THAT IT WAS FOR MY OWN GOOD.
WHY IS THAT?
WHY CAN'T WE SEE EACH OTHER?
Dr. Kurahashi: FOR STARTERS,
I SHOULD TELL YOU
WHAT THE MEDICUBOID IS ABOUT.
Asuna: OKAY.
Dr. Kurahashi:
MEDICUBOID IS THE CODE NAME
FOR THE WORLD'S FIRST
MEDICAL FULL‐DIVE MACHINE.
IT'S SO REVOLUTIONARY,
THE GOVERNMENT'S
BACKING ITS DEVELOPMENT.
Asuna: IT'S A FULL‐DIVE RIG
FOR HOSPITALS?
Dr. Kurahashi: UH‐HUH.
FOR EXAMPLE,
LET'S SAY YOU WERE A PATIENT
WITH A VISUAL
OR HEARING DISABILITY.
THIS MACHINE
CAN GIVE YOU BACK THOSE SENSES.
YOU KNOW HOW
WITH THE AMUSPHERE RIG
IMAGES AND SOUNDS GET SENT
DIRECTLY TO YOUR BRAIN?
WELL, TRANSMITTING SIGNALS
ISN'T ALL IT DOES.
THE AMUSPHERE HAS THE ABILITY
TO CANCEL OUT
PHYSICAL SENSATIONS, TOO.
BACK HERE, IT HITS THAT SPOT
WITH ELECTROMAGNETIC PULSES,
SO IT TEMPORARILY
NUMBS THE NERVES.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE
A GENERAL ANESTHETIC.
Asuna: OKAY, BUT HOW IS THAT
USEFUL FOR HOSPITALS?
THERE'S A LIMIT TO HOW MUCH
THE AMUSPHERE CAN BLOCK OUT.
WHAT HAPPENS IF A PATIENT'S
IN SERIOUS PAIN?
Dr. Kurahashi: EXACTLY.
YOU HIT THE NAIL
RIGHT ON THE HEAD.
THE AMUSPHERE CAN'T DO IT.
EVEN THE NERVEGEAR
CAN'T BLOCK PAIN
FROM SURGERY OR CHRONIC ILLNESS.
HOWEVER, THE MEDICUBOID ENHANCES
THE ELECTROMAGNETIC PULSE.
PLUS IT'S BUILT INTO THE BED,
SO THERE'S MORE COVERAGE,
THE BRAIN, SPINE, EVERYTHING.
ONCE IT GETS ON THE MARKET,
IT'LL CHANGE THE COURSE
OF MEDICINE AS WE KNOW IT.
THE MEDICUBOID
HAS INCREDIBLE POTENTIAL.
YOU COULD, SAY,
PAIR IT WITH A CAMERA
AND GIVE IT AN A. R. FUNCTION.
THE PATIENT GETS
REAL‐WORLD IMAGES IN REAL TIME.
Asuna: THAT'S GREAT.
SOUNDS MORE LIKE A MIRACLE
THAN A MACHINE TO ME.
Dr. Kurahashi: YES.
IN A WAY, IT IS A MIRACLE.
EVEN SO, CURING ILLNESS
IS SOMETHING IT CAN'T DO.
THE MEDICUBOID
IS MAKING AN IMPACT, THOUGH,
WE HOPE, IN TERMINAL CARE.
Asuna: TERMINAL CARE?
Dr. Kurahashi: YES.
IT'S HELPING
PATIENTS WHO ARE DYING.
Asuna: (GASPS) SHE'S DYING?
Dr. Kurahashi: YUUKI TOLD ME
THAT IF YOU
REALLY WANTED TO HEAR
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HER,
I COULD GO AHEAD AND TELL YOU,
BUT I HAVE TO WARN YOU,
IT'S NOT A PLEASANT STORY.
YOU'RE GOING TO WISH
THIS CONVERSATION ENDED
RIGHT HERE.
Asuna: (GASPS)
NO...
I WANT TO HEAR IT,
THE WHOLE THING,
AND I'M NOT LEAVING HERE
UNTIL YOU TELL ME.
Dr. Kurahashi:
YUUKI WAS BORN IN MAY OF 2011,
BUT THERE WERE COMPLICATIONS,
AND THE DOCTORS HAD TO GIVE
HER MOTHER A C‐SECTION.
HER MOTHER WAS GIVEN
A TRANSFUSION
DURING THE PROCEDURE,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY
THE BLOOD THEY USED
‐ WAS CONTAMINATED WITH A VIRUS.
‐ Asuna: (GASPS)
Dr. Kurahashi: THEY DIDN'T
FIND OUT ABOUT IT
UNTIL SEPTEMBER, WHEN HER MOTHER
WAS HAVING TESTS RUN
FOR AN INFECTION SHE GOT.
BUT BY THAT TIME,
THE WHOLE FAMILY'D
BEEN INFECTED.
THIS WAY.
WE HAVE TO KEEP THE ROOM
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE GLASS
HERMETICALLY SEALED,
SO THIS IS
AS CLOSE AS YOU CAN GET.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND.
Asuna: (GASPS)
YUUKI.
DOCTOR, WHAT KIND OF ILLNESS
DOES YUUKI HAVE?
Dr. Kurahashi: ACQUIRED
IMMUNE DEFICIENCY SYNDROME,
AIDS FOR SHORT.
Asuna: (GASPS)
Dr. Kurahashi: IT'S CAUSED
BY THE H. I. V. VIRUS.
IT'S SCARY, BUT THERE'S HOPE,
BECAUSE NOT EVERYONE
WHO HAS IT DEVELOPS AIDS.
IF YOU CAN TREAT H. I. V. EARLY,
YOU CAN HAVE A LONG LIFE.
(LENS WHIRS)
IN HER FAMILY'S CASE,
THE VIRUS
WAS DIFFICULT TO TREAT.
IT'S A DRUG‐RESISTANT STRAIN.
WHEN HER MOTHER FOUND OUT,
SHE GOT SO UPSET
OVER HER CHILDREN'S FATE,
SHE ACTUALLY CONSIDERED
KILLING THE WHOLE FAMILY
ALONG WITH HERSELF.
BUT THEN SHE CHANGED HER MIND
AND DECIDED
TO FIGHT THE DISEASE INSTEAD.
Asuna: SHE FOUGHT IT
FOR HER KIDS.
Dr. Kurahashi: YES.
SOON AFTER THEY WERE DIAGNOSED,
YUUKI WAS PUT ON A MULTIDRUG
COURSE OF THERAPY,
BUT IT'S HARD FOR A CHILD
TO HAVE TO TAKE
SO MANY DIFFERENT MEDICATIONS
AND KEEP TAKING THEM.
THE SIDE‐EFFECTS ARE ONE THING.
THE OTHER, BEING SHUNNED
BY PEOPLE WHO DON'T UNDERSTAND
HER CONDITION.
STILL, YUUKI WAS A TROUPER.
SHE BELIEVED HER
AND HER FAMILY
WOULD GET BETTER EVENTUALLY.
HOWEVER, WHEN SHE
WAS IN THE FOURTH GRADE,
HER IMMUNE SYSTEM
SUDDENLY COLLAPSED,
AND THEN SHE WAS BROUGHT
TO THIS HOSPITAL,
AND THAT'S WHEN SHE
WAS DIAGNOSED WITH AIDS.
Asuna: (SHUDDERS)
Dr. Kurahashi: BUT LIKE I SAID,
SHE'S A TROUPER.
SHE NEVER ONCE LOST
HER OPTIMISM.
Asuna: DOCTOR...
Dr. Kurahashi: HMM?
Asuna: WHY IS SHE USING
THE MEDICUBOID?
Dr. Kurahashi: I GUESS
YOU COULD SAY IT ALL STARTED
BACK WHEN EVERYONE WAS PANICKING
OVER THAT NERVEGEAR INCIDENT.
THEY HAD JUST COMPLETED
THE FIRST PROTOTYPE
OF THE MEDICUBOID.
THE ELECTROMAGNETIC PULSES
IT PUT OUT
WERE MANY TIMES STRONGER
THAN THE NERVEGEAR'S.
THAT WAS A PROBLEM,
SINCE NO ONE KNEW
WHAT THE LONG‐TERM EFFECTS
OF EXPOSURE WERE.
BECAUSE OF THAT,
THEY COULDN'T FIND A PATIENT
WILLING TO TAKE THE RISK,
SO ITS TRIAL RUN WAS STALLED.
WHEN I FOUND OUT,
I THOUGHT
ABOUT YUUKI'S SITUATION,
AND I CONTACTED HER PARENTS.
IF SHE WERE THE TEST SUBJECT,
SHE'D BE MOVED
TO THE MEDICUBOID STERILE ROOM.
SHE'D RUN LESS OF A RISK
OF GETTING AN INFECTION.
I TOLD THEM IT WAS
A GREAT OPPORTUNITY.
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
BUT HONESTLY, I STILL DON'T KNOW
IF I WAS RIGHT TO SUGGEST IT.
GOD KNOWS WHAT IT WAS LIKE
FOR YUUKI AND HER PARENTS,
THINKING ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT TO ACCEPT.
BUT I THINK
THE LURE OF THE UNKNOWN,
THE VIRTUAL WORLD WAS
THE DECIDING FACTOR FOR YUUKI,
SO THAT BRAVE LITTLE GIRL
AGREED TO BE A TEST SUBJECT,
AND THEY MOVED HER IN.
SHE'S LIVED INSIDE
THE MEDICUBOID EVER SINCE.
Asuna: YOU MEAN
SHE'S NEVER COME OUT?
Dr. Kurahashi: NO, SHE HASN'T.
YUUKI STAYS LOGGED IN
AND RARELY SPENDS ANY TIME
IN THE REAL WORLD.
SHE'S ALWAYS IN A LOT OF PAIN,
BUT THANKS TO THE MEDICUBOID'S
SENSATION CANCELER,
SHE CAN BLOCK IT OUT.
Asuna: SO WAIT. YOU MEAN SHE'S
IN A CONTINUOUS, 24‐HOUR DIVE?
SINCE WHEN?
Dr. Kurahashi:
FOR THREE YEARS NOW.
Asuna: THAT'S A WHOLE YEAR
LONGER THAN US.
Kirito: IT FELT
LIKE THEY WERE A PRODUCT
OF THE FULL‐DIVE
ENVIRONMENT ITSELF.
Asuna: THANK YOU, DOCTOR.
I'M GLAD I GOT TO SEE HER AGAIN.
SHE'LL BE OKAY
AS LONG AS SHE'S HERE, RIGHT?
Dr. Kurahashi: WE'RE DOING
EVERYTHING WE CAN FOR HER,
BUT EVEN IF THE ROOM IS STERILE,
THERE'S NO WAY TO ELIMINATE
THE VIRUS THAT'S INSIDE HER.
Asuna: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Dr. Kurahashi: YUUKI DOESN'T
HAVE MUCH TIME LEFT.
Asuna: (GASPS)
Dr. Kurahashi: AND THAT'S
MOST LIKELY THE REASON
WHY SHE TRIED CUTTING TIES
WITH YOU THE WAY SHE DID.
Asuna: THAT'S WHY SHE...
YUUKI!
Yuuki: ASUNA, I‐‐I...
(LAUGHS) WE DID IT!
LEAVE IT TO ME, SIS!
Asuna: (GASPS)
UM, DOCTOR, I WAS WONDERING,
DOES YUUKI HAVE AN OLDER SISTER?
Dr. Kurahashi:
UH, YES, ACTUALLY,
A TWIN SISTER, TO BE PRECISE.
HER NAME'S AIKO,
AND SHE WAS BORN
A FEW MINUTES EARLIER.
YUUKI WAS THE CHEERFUL ONE.
IN FACT, AIKO WOULD JUST SIT
AND WATCH HER AND SMILE.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
IF AIKO WERE HERE, I'D IMAGINE
SHE'D BE A LOT LIKE YOU.
Asuna: WHERE IS SHE?
Dr. Kurahashi: YUUKI'S PARENTS
PASSED AWAY TWO YEARS AGO,
AND LAST YEAR, AIKO.
Asuna: (CRYING) YUUKI.
YUUKI.
Yuuki: (SIGHS)
DON'T CRY, ASUNA.
Asuna: HUH?
YUUKI.
YUUKI! YOU CAN HEAR ME?!
Yuuki: YEAH, I CAN HEAR YOU.
I CAN SEE YOU, TOO.
WOW, YOU LOOK EXACTLY
LIKE YOU DO IN THE GAME.
THANKS FOR COMING TO SEE ME.
Asuna: YUUKI.
I JUST‐‐I DON'T...
Yuuki: HEY, DOC,
WOULD IT BE OKAY
IF ASUNA USED
THE ROOM NEXT‐DOOR?
Asuna: (GASPS)
Dr. Kurahashi: SURE. WHY NOT?
I KEEP AN AMUSPHERE IN THERE
SO I CAN VISIT HER.
GO AHEAD. IT'S ALL YOURS.
Asuna: THANKS.
Yuuki: THE "A. L. O." APP'S
ON THE START‐UP MENU.
AFTER YOU LOG IN,
COME TO THE PLACE
WHERE WE FIRST MET, OKAY?
(CHORUS SINGING)
Asuna: I WANT TO SEE YOU.
I WANT TO SEE YOU ONE MORE TIME!
I WANT TO SEE YOU,
AND THIS TIME,
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU FOR REAL.
YUUKI!
(GASPS)
YUUKI.
(LAUGHS)
Yuuki: I KNEW IT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU DID IT,
BUT I HAD A FEELING
YOU'D FIND ME
IN THE REAL WORLD SOMEHOW.
AND I WAS SO CAREFUL
NOT TO SAY NOTHIN',
THOUGHT I HAD YOU FOOLED.
IT DIDN'T WORK.
YOU FOUND ME ANYWAY.
I MUST BE TURNING PSYCHIC,
'CAUSE MY PREDICTIONS
NEVER COME TRUE.
BUT I'M HAPPY, REALLY.
Asuna: (GASPS)
(SHUDDERS)
Yuuki: MY SIS USED
TO HUG ME LIKE THIS.
YOU SMELL LIKE HER,
LIKE THE SUN.
Asuna: DID AIKO PLAY
V. R. M. M. O. s WITH YOU, TOO?
Yuuki: YUP. IN FACT,
SHE WAS THE FIRST LEADER
THE SLEEPING KNIGHTS EVER HAD.
AND IF YOU THOUGHT I WAS STRONG,
MAN, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN HER.
WE MET SIUNE AND THE OTHER GUYS
IN THIS VIRTUAL HOSPICE
CALLED THE SERENE GARDEN.
BACK THEN,
THERE WERE NINE OF US,
BUT MY SIS
AND CLOVIS AND MERIDA,
WELL, THEY'RE ALL GONE.
Asuna: (GASPS)
Yuuki: ANYWAY,
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHY WE'RE DISBANDING, IT'S CAUSE
WE PROMISED EACH OTHER
IF WE LOST SOMEONE,
WE'D END IT.
I'M SORRY, ASUNA.
THAT'S WHY I COULDN'T TELL YOU.
THE SLEEPING KNIGHTS WON'T BE
AROUND ANYMORE BY THIS SPRING,
BUT IT'S NOT 'CAUSE WE'LL ALL BE
TOO BUSY TO PLAY ANYMORE.
IT'S 'CAUSE A LITTLE WHILE AGO,
TWO OF US GOT THE NEWS
FROM OUR DOCTORS.
THEY GAVE US THREE MONTHS.
Asuna: (GASPS)
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
Yuuki: YOU SEE, THAT'S WHY
WE WERE ALL SO FIRED UP
ON HAVING ONE LAST BIG ADVENTURE
TOGETHER IN THIS WORLD.
WE WANTED TO LEAVE SOME KIND
OF PROOF WE WERE HERE
ON THAT BIG OLD MONUMENT
WHERE EVERYONE CAN SEE IT,
ONE LAST RUN THAT WAS SO COOL,
WE COULD BRAG ABOUT IT
TO MY SIS AND THE OTHERS.
BUT NOTHING
WAS GOING RIGHT FOR US,
SO WE DECIDED
THE BEST WAY TO GET THERE
WAS TO GET SOMEONE
TOUGH ENOUGH TO HELP.
BUT WE JUST CAUSED YOU TROUBLE,
AND WE HURT YOUR FEELINGS, TOO.
I'M SORRY.
WE ALL ARE.
FORGET ABOUT US.
IT'S PROBABLY
FOR THE BEST, ANYWAY.
Asuna: I CAN'T DO THAT.
I'M HAPPY I GOT TO MEET YOU,
ALL OF YOU,
AND I'M GLAD I GOT TO BE
A PART OF YOUR LAST QUEST.
EVEN AFTER EVERYTHING,
I STILL WISH
I COULD JOIN THE KNIGHTS.
Yuuki: YEAH, I WISH‐‐
I WISH YOU COULD, TOO,
BUT I'M HAPPY I CAME HERE
AND GOT TO MEET YOU.
YOU SAYING THAT
MAKES IT WORTH IT,
MORE THAN WORTH IT.
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR ME.
I'M GOOD.
Asuna: BUT ISN'T THERE
ANYTHING ELSE YOU WANT TO DO?
I MEAN, I'M SURE THERE'S
LOTS OF PLACES IN ALFHEIM
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN YET
AND OTHER VIRTUAL WORLDS.
THERE'S STILL LOTS OF THINGS
TO DO AND PLACES TO SEE.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME
YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH.
Yuuki: FOR THE LAST THREE YEARS,
WE GOT TO GO ON TONS
OF ADVENTURES IN OTHER WORLDS.
BUT I WANT MY VERY LAST MEMORY
TO BE THE ONE I GOT TO GO ON
WITH YOU, ASUNA.
Asuna: YEAH, BUT CAN'T YOU
THINK OF ANYTHING ELSE
YOU WANT TO SEE OR MAYBE DO?
Yuuki: I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS MAYBE
GO TO SCHOOL AGAIN.
Asuna: UH, FOR REAL?
Yuuki: NAH, FORGET IT.
JUST KIDDING.
I'M HAPPY YOU WANT TO HELP,
BUT DON'T SWEAT IT.
IT'S COOL.
I HAD AN AWESOME LIFE, REALLY.
Asuna: MAYBE YOU CAN.
Yuuki: WAIT. WHAT?
Asuna: MAYBE YOU CAN GO,
YOU KNOW, TO SCHOOL!