Kirito: ( GRUNTING )
Death Gun: ( LAUGHS )
Kirito: DAMN IT. HE'S TOUGH.
IF I CAN SLOW HIM DOWN,
ONE SECOND'S ALL I NEED.
Sinon: KIRITO!
IF ONLY I HAD MY SCOPE.
Kirito: I GET IT NOW.
THERE ARE THINGS
I SHOULDN'T FORGET,
WHAT IT MEANS TO KILL,
THE SIGNIFICANCE
OF TAKING A LIFE,
AND ONCE I ACCEPT IT,
MAYBE THEN I'LL BE ABLE
TO FIND SOME CLOSURE.
THAT'S HOW I SEE IT.
Sinon: RIGHT NOW,
KIRITO'S TRYING TO GET
THAT CLOSURE
HE WAS TALKING ABOUT.
HE'S CONFRONTING
HIS DEMONS FROM "S. A. O."
BY TAKING ON THE PERSON
WHO REPRESENTS THEM, DEATH GUN.
AND THE REASON HE CAN
ISN'T 'CAUSE HE'S STRONG.
IT'S 'CAUSE HE ACCEPTS
WHAT HE DID,
EVEN THOUGH
IT STILL TEARS HIM UP,
AND HE'S STILL TRYING
TO MOVE ON DESPITE IT.
( GROANS )
I GOTTA DO SOMETHING.
THINK!
( GASPS )
Asuna: KIRITO.
Kirito: ( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Aki: HE'S SWEATING SO MUCH.
HE'LL DEHYDRATE SOON.
I WONDER IF WE CAN GET HIM
TO LOG OUT OR AT LEAST WARN HIM.
Asuna: NO, HE WOULDN'T HEAR US.
THE DIVE BLOCKS EVERYTHING OUT.
THE AMUSPHERE IS DESIGNED
WITH STUFF LIKE THIS IN MIND,
SO IT SHOULD SHUT OFF
IF HE GETS TOO DEHYDRATED.
Aki: OKAY, THEN.
I GUESS WE JUST HAVE TO WAIT.
Yui: HEY, MOMMY,
TRY HOLDING DADDY'S HAND.
HE'LL FEEL
THE WARMTH OF YOUR TOUCH
AND KNOW YOU'RE HERE
WATCHING OVER HIM.
SINCE I CAN'T TOUCH ANYTHING
IN YOUR WORLD,
HOLD IT FOR ME, TOO.
I KNOW HE WON'T FEEL ME THERE,
BUT STILL.
Asuna: NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I'M SURE HE'LL FEEL
YOUR HAND, TOO.
I KNOW HE WILL.
WE'LL CHEER HIM ON TOGETHER.
Yui: MOMMY.
Asuna: HANG IN THERE, KIRITO.
FIGHT FOR WHAT YOU BELIEVE IN,
AND I'LL BE RIGHT HERE
BY YOUR SIDE.
WHEREVER YOU GO
AND WHATEVER YOU DO,
I'LL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
Kirito: ( GRUNTING )
HE'S RIGHT.
I DIDN'T WANT TO KNOW HIS NAME.
I DIDN'T WANT
ANYTHING TO DO WITH HIM.
BUT I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
I WOULDN'T BE RID OF HIM
THAT EASY.
I DIDN'T FORGET.
I ONLY PRETENDED TO.
BUT I WAS JUST FOOLING MYSELF.
RED EYES.
I SAW THEM IN THE BRIEFING
BEFORE THE RAID.
BLACK.
RED.
XAXA.
Death Gun: ( GASPS )
Kirito: RED‐EYED XAXA,
THAT'S YOU! THAT'S YOUR NAME!
Death Gun: ( GASPS )
Sinon: KIRITO!
Kirito: SINON'S DISTRACTING HIM
WITH HER BULLET LINE.
SHE'S GOT HIM IN HER SIGHTS,
USING ALL HER SKILL AND SPIRIT
TO KEEP IT TRAINED ON HIM.
IT'S LIKE A PHANTOM BULLET.
ONE LAST ATTACK!
I CAN'T WASTE THIS CHANCE!
( YELLS )
Death Gun: ( LAUGHS )
Kirito: ( YELLS )
Death Gun: ( GROWLS )
Kirito: ( YELLING )
Death Gun: ( GASPS )
Kirito: ( PANTING )
Death Gun: FOOL.
IT'S NOT OVER YET.
YOU CAN'T STOP ME.
HE'LL FIND YOU,
AND HE'LL...
Kirito: NO, XAXA, YOU'RE DONE,
AND WE'LL FIND
YOUR PARTNER, TOO.
HE WON'T KILL ANYONE ANYMORE.
LAUGHING COFFIN'S DEAD.
( WIND BLOWING )
Asuna: ( SIGHS )
KIRITO.
Yui: DADDY.
Kirito: IT'S OVER.
Sinon: YEAH.
Kirito: I GUESS NOW
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET THIS TOURNEY OVER WITH, HUH?
Sinon: YEAH, WE SHOULD.
Kirito: WITH DEATH GUN
OUT OF THE PICTURE,
I'M PRETTY SURE
THE GUY CASING OUT
YOUR APARTMENT'S TAKEN OFF.
Sinon: HMM.
Kirito: I DON'T THINK YOU'LL BE
IN ANY DANGER WHEN YOU LOG OUT,
BUT YOU SHOULD CALL THE COPS
WHEN YOU DO, JUST TO BE SAFE.
Sinon: OKAY, BUT WHAT
AM I SUPPOSED TO TELL THEM?
Kirito: OH, YEAH. RIGHT.
THE GUY I WORK FOR
IS WITH THE GOVERNMENT.
I COULD ASK HIM TO SEND
THE COPS TO YOUR PLACE,
BUT HOW AM I
GONNA GET YOUR INFO?
I CAN'T REALLY
ASK FOR IT IN HERE.
Sinon: IT'S COOL.
I'LL TELL YOU.
Kirito: HUH? ARE YOU SURE?
Sinon: MY NAME IS SHINO,
SHINO ASADA,
AND I LIVE AT...
Kirito: YOU'RE NOT
GONNA BELIEVE THIS,
BUT YOU'RE CLOSE
TO THE PLACE I'M DIVING FROM.
Sinon: YEAH? WOW, NO WAY.
Kirito: HOW 'BOUT THIS?
AFTER WE LOG OUT,
I COULD HEAD OVER TO YOU.
Sinon: YOU WOULD? REALLY?
OH.
NO, I'M GOOD.
A FRIEND OF MINE LIVES NEAR ME,
SO I'VE GOT HELP IF I NEED IT.
Kirito: OKAY,
BUT AFTER I LOG OUT,
I'LL CALL THE GUY I WORK FOR
AND HAVE HIM SEND THE COPS
IF YOU'RE COOL WITH THAT.
Sinon: MM‐HMM. SOUNDS GOOD.
BUT NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
YOU JUST GONNA LOG OUT
WITHOUT TELLING ME YOUR INFO?
Kirito: OH, RIGHT. SORRY.
MY REAL NAME IS KAZUTO KIRIGAYA.
Sinon: THAT'S HOW
YOU GOT "KIRITO"? SERIOUSLY?
TALK ABOUT
A LACK OF IMAGINATION.
Kirito: YEAH, WELL,
LIKE YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
Sinon: HMM?
( LAUGHS )
Kirito: ( LAUGHS )
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
IF WE'RE EVER GONNA
LOG OUT OF THIS THING,
WE'VE GOTTA END B. o. B. FIRST.
SO HOW DO YOU WANNA DO THIS?
WANT TO HAVE A DUEL
LIKE WE DID YESTERDAY?
Sinon: HMM.
LOOK AT YOURSELF.
YOU'RE ALL BANGED UP.
THERE'S NO CHALLENGE
IN BEATING SOMEONE
WHO'S ALREADY
AS THRASHED AS YOU.
NAH. I'LL TAKE YOU ON
AT THE NEXT B. o. B,
BUT YOU BETTER
NOT LEAVE ME HANGING.
Kirito: ( GROANS )
Sinon: WELL, LET'S GET
THIS THING OVER WITH ALREADY.
Kirito: HOW WE GONNA DO THAT?
UNLESS ONE OF OUR H.P.s
DRAINS OUT ALL THE WAY,
THERE'S NOT GONNA BE A WINNER.
Sinon: I GUESS YOU DIDN'T HEAR
WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE FIRST B. o. B.
THERE WERE TWO WINNERS.
THE PLAYER WHO SHOULD HAVE WON
LET HIS GUARD DOWN TOO SOON,
SO HIS OPPONENT GAVE HIM
WHAT WE CALL A SOUVENIR GRENADE.
Kirito: A SOUVENIR GRENADE?
WHAT THE HECK'S THAT?
Sinon: THIS.
( BEEPING )
Kirito: ( GASPING )
Sinon: ( LAUGHS )
Kirito: UH...
Kirito: ( CHUCKLES )
( MUSIC PLAYING )
Players: ( CHEERING )
( TIMER BEEPING )
Kirito: DEATH GUN
HAD TWO VICTIMS THIS TIME.
THAT MEANS HE'S GOT
AT LEAST TWO OTHERS HELPING HIM.
Sinon: ( SIGHS )
( GASPING )
( SNEEZES )
( BED CREAKS )
( GASPS )
WHAT AM I DOING?
( SIGHS )
‐ ( DOORBELL RINGS )
‐ ( GASPS )
( DOORBELL RINGS )
Kyoji: ASADA? YOU THERE?
IT'S ME, ASADA.
Sinon: SHINKAWA.
Kyoji: I, UH, JUST WANTED
TO CONGRATULATE YOU ON YOUR WIN.
I EVEN BROUGHT SOME PASTRIES.
AND, HEY, CONGRATS.
YOU WERE SO AWESOME, ASADA.
I MEAN SINON.
YOU DID IT.
YOU'RE THE BEST GUNNER
IN "G. G. O." NOW.
Sinon: ( GIGGLES )
Kyoji: I KNEW ALL ALONG
YOU COULD DO IT.
YOU DESERVE BEING NUMBER ONE
MORE THAN ANYBODY.
YOU SHOWED THEM ALL
WHAT REAL STRENGTH'S ABOUT.
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD.
Sinon: THANK YOU.
Kyoji: UM, ASADA...
Sinon: WHAT'S UP?
Kyoji: YOU SAID‐‐
YOU SAID TO WAIT.
REMEMBER THAT?
Sinon: WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
Kyoji: WELL, YOU TOLD ME TO WAIT
AND, IF I DID,
THEN YOU'D BE MINE.
Sinon: HUH?
Kyoji: I WAITED.
I WAITED FOR YOU.
Sinon: WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
Kyoji: FROM NOW ON,
I'LL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
YOU DON'T NEED HIM
TO PROTECT YOU.
THAT'S MY JOB.
I'M GONNA PROTECT YOU NOW...
FOREVER.
Sinon: ( GASPS )
SHINKAWA!
Kyoji: I LOVE YOU, ASADA.
YOU'RE MINE, MY ASADA,
MY SINON, MINE.
Sinon: ( GASPING ) LET GO!
Kyoji: HUH?
WHY'D YOU
PUSH ME AWAY LIKE THAT?
YOU MADE A PROMISE.
WE BOTH DID.
Sinon: SHINKAWA.
SH‐SHINKAWA.
Kyoji: DON'T MAKE
ANY SUDDEN MOVES, ASADA.
THE SYRINGE I'M HOLDING'S
GOT A DRUG IN IT
THAT'LL PARALYZE YOUR MUSCLES
IN AN INSTANT.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, YOUR LUNGS
WILL STOP, THEN YOUR HEART.
Sinon: SYRINGE?
Kirito: MAYBE BY INJECTING
SOME KIND OF DRUG OR SOMETHING.
THAT'S ONE WAY.
Kyoji: YEAH,
IT IS THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
I PROMISED MY DAD
I'D GO TO MED SCHOOL,
SO IT'S A DONE DEAL.
STUCK WITH IT NOW.
Sinon: THIS IS CRAZY.
YOU'RE THE OTHER DEATH GUN?
Kyoji: OOH, I'M IMPRESSED.
YOU FIGURED OUT
DEATH GUN'S LITTLE SECRET.
IT'S TRUE.
I'M DEATH GUN'S
PARTNER IN CRIME.
Sinon: ( GASPING )
Kyoji: UP TO NOW,
BEFORE THIS YEAR'S B. o. B.,
ANYWAY,
I WAS THE ONE PLAYING STERBEN,
BUT TODAY I INSISTED ON BEING
THE ONE TO DO THE JOB I. R. L.
DON'T YOU SEE I HAD TO BE
THE ONE DOING THE DEED?
I CAN'T LET
SOME OTHER GUY TOUCH YOU,
EVEN IF THAT GUY IS MY BROTHER.
Sinon: YOUR BROTHER?
SO THEN THE PLAYER
WHO BELONGED
TO THAT MURDER GUILD
IN "S. A. O.,"
THAT WAS YOUR OLDER BROTHER.
Kyoji: FORGET ABOUT HIM.
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME NOW, ASADA.
Sinon: ( GASPS ) STOP.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
WHAT ABOUT CRAM SCHOOL, HUH?
YOU SAID YOU WERE
GONNA BE A DOCTOR.
Kyoji: DOCTOR?
YOU THINK
I GIVE A DAMN ABOUT THAT,
ABOUT MY PARENTS,
THOSE GUYS AT SCHOOL?
THEY'RE ALL ASSHOLES!
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD
HAVE MADE ME HAPPY?
TO BE THE STRONGEST PLAYER
IN "G. G. O.,"
BUT THAT PIECE OF SHIT ZXE‐D
LIED ABOUT AGI TYPES
BEING THE STRONGEST,
AND I FELL FOR IT LIKE AN IDIOT!
YOU DON'T KNOW.
"G.G.O." WAS EVERYTHING TO ME,
AND I GAVE EVERYTHING UP
IN THE REAL WORLD FOR IT,
GOD DAMN IT!
Sinon: Y‐YOU KILLED ZXE‐D
'CAUSE HE LIED?
Kyoji: OH, COME ON.
HE WAS THE PERFECT VICTIM.
WE HAD TO SHOW THE WORLD
DEATH GUN WAS
THE STRONGEST IN "G. G. O.,"
IN ALL THE V. R. M. M. O. s.
WHAT BETTER PERSON TO SACRIFICE
THAN THAT DORK?
AND NOW THAT THAT'S DONE,
I DON'T NEED
THIS REALITY ANYMORE.
LET'S MOVE ON TO THE NEXT ONE.
COME ON, JUST YOU AND ME.
Sinon: WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
Kyoji: WE CAN GO
SOMEWHERE LIKE "G. G. O."
MM. NO, SOMEPLACE
WITH A FANTASY VIBE INSTEAD.
AS LONG AS IT'S WITH YOU,
I DON'T CARE.
WE'LL BE REBORN,
BE HUSBAND AND WIFE.
WE'LL GET A HOUSE.
WE'LL GO ON QUESTS TOGETHER,
OH, AND HAVE KIDS, TOO.
IT'LL BE SO MUCH FUN.
I KNOW IT WILL. COME WITH ME.
ASADA.
YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
YOU ARE.
MORE THAN ANYTHING,
YOU'RE MINE AND NO ONE ELSE'S.
I ALWAYS LOVED YOU, ASADA,
ALWAYS.
IN SCHOOL, WHEN I HEARD
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED,
WHEN I HEARD WHAT YOU DID,
I COULD LOOK ALL OVER AND NEVER
FIND ANOTHER GIRL LIKE YOU.
I MEAN, YOU SHOT A REAL BAD GUY
WITH A REAL GUN AND KILLED HIM!
HOW COOL IS THAT?
I TOLD YOU, DIDN'T I?
I SAID YOU HAD REAL POWER.
WHEN I CAME UP
WITH THE DEATH GUN LEGEND,
I PICKED THE TYPE 54
AS HIS GUN 'CAUSE OF YOU.
THAT'S HOW MUCH
I LOVE YOU, ASADA.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH,
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
Sinon: ( WHIMPERING ) NO.
Robber: ( LAUGHING )
Sinon: I DON'T WANT
TO SEE ANYTHING
OR FEEL ANYTHING ANYMORE.
THIS ISN'T REAL.
IT CAN'T BE.
KIRITO.
YOU WENT TO ALL THAT TROUBLE
TO SAVE ME,
BUT IT WAS ALL FOR NOTHING.
Kirito: HOW 'BOUT THIS?
AFTER WE LOG OUT,
I COULD HEAD OVER TO YOU.
Sinon: ( GASPS )
IF HE COMES OVER,
HE'LL BE IN DANGER.
AND I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT IT.
Avatar: THAT'S NOT TRUE.
Sinon: HUH?
Avatar: UP TO THIS POINT,
ALL WE'VE BEEN DOING WAS
LOOKING OUT FOR OURSELVES.
WE CERTAINLY NEVER FOUGHT
FOR ANYONE ELSE.
BUT NOW, EVEN THOUGH
IT MIGHT BE TOO LATE FOR US,
LET'S GO FIGHT FOR SOMEONE ELSE,
JUST THIS ONCE, ME AND YOU.
Sinon: ( SIGHS )
Avatar: ( CHUCKLES )
COME ON. LET'S GO.
Sinon: ( WHIMPERS )
Kyoji: I LOVE YOU, ASADA.
Both: ( GRUNTING )
Sinon: ( YELPS )
Kyoji: A‐ASADA!
Sinon: NO.
LET GO OF ME! NO!
Kyoji: ASADA. ASADA.
ASADA! ASADA!
‐ ASADA! ASADA!
‐ Sinon: ( SCREAMS)
Kyoji: ASADA!
Sinon: ( GASPS )
Both: ( GRUNTING )
Kirito: RUN, SINON!
Sinon: KIRITO.