Whooo, alright!!
This feels awesome!
[CHELSEA]
Hahaha...
You're so innocent
I can't believe you're
a killer, Tatsumi.
It's funny.
I'd never expect that!
[LEONE]
Wow! This is even
more of a blast
than I thought!
[AKAME]
Yeah. The view is really
something. This is nice.
[Trembling]
[MINE]
THIS ISN'T NICE AT ALL!
[Roar]
[NAJENDA]
The Marg Highlands are
crawling with Danger Beasts,
which makes it impossible
for humans to live here.
And that's why it's a perfect
place to build our new hideout.
The Revolutionary Army's recon
unit is currently searching
for a more permanent place
for us near the capital,
but they haven't found anything.
So until we hear from them
we'll just stay right here
and level ourselves up.
[MINE]
Hey, look!
It's leaving; should we
try to catch it?
[CHELSEA]
It's going back to
its nest at HQ, silly!
Well, Mine, I'm surprised
you weren't smart enough
to figure that out.
Hahaha...
Oh great.
I hate you already!
Oh yes, I haven't given our new
members a proper introduction.
I'd like you to meet‐ Huh?
I already knew you were cute,
but you're adorable from
up close, Akame!
Why are you touching me?
Oh, yes, my name's Chelsea.
Since we're going to be
killing people together,
I hope we all get along.
Here! This is for you.
Oh!
[AKAME]
Welcome to the team.
Did she just win Akame's
heart with a lollipop?!
That long flight must have
made her REALLY hungry!
You know, Chelsea seems
even less likely to be
a cold‐blooded assassin
than Mine and
the others girls do.
Don't judge a book
by its cover.
She's an expert killer
who's completed just
as many jobs as Akame.
[TATSUMI]
Eh?
As for this fellow,
headquarters has entrusted
him with me as well.
Everyone meet the
Lightning Fast Susanoo,
he's my new Imperial Arms.
Organic types are mostly
autonomous, so he shouldn't
be all that draining.
Even with all my injuries
I can still use him.
Uh... Hi, I think
we met earlier.
Ah!
Uh, hey now‐
Fixed!
[NAJENDA]
I should warn you,
he's a bit of a neat freak.
[MINE]
Yeah, no kidding...
Well now I get why he
fixed my hair before.
Okay. So, what exactly
is his primary ability?
Does he only do
hand‐to‐hand combat?
Hehe...
Allow me to demonstrate
that for you.
Try to contain your excitement.
Susanoo, proceed!
Understood.
[LUBBOCK]
Okay I admit, that DOES
look impressive, but...
what is he doing?
[TATSUMI]
From where I'm standing
it looks like... chores.
Wonderful, isn't he?!
Susanoo's original purpose
was to protect royalty
and others of status.
Not only can he fight,
he's equipped with a full range
of cleaning and cooking skills
so he never has to leave
his owner's side!
He can do it all!
And the best part is,
his menu includes a
thousand different dishes!
How is any of that gonna
help us in a fight?!
Now, now, I'm sure you'll
come to appreciate it.
Last but not least...
he also possesses a
trump card for combat.
Don't you?
Yeah.
[TATSUMI]
So these are my two
new teammates, huh?
They seem pretty reliable.
‐Oh my goodness, you're flat
as a board, aren't you?
‐SHUT UP!
Y'know, you may be all
big and handsome and
strong and everything,
but you're still just
a glorified man‐maid!
[TATSUMI]
Hope our teamwork
isn't gonna suffer.
[Door opens, footsteps]
[RUN]
We've finished searching
the doctor's residence.
However, we were unable to find
any evidence as to what caused
his sudden disappearance.
[BOLS]
We did notice none of his
valuable research materials
or equipment went missing
from the laboratory, though.
[ESDEATH]
If he hasn't deserted us,
that means he must
have been killed.
[BOLS]
And none of his
enhanced soldiers
were anywhere to
be found either.
I can only assume they
were all killed as well.
[ESDEATH]
I understand.
Poor Seryu's lost another
person she looked up to.
[Koro whines]
Are you going to
be able to handle
your maintenance without
the doctor's help?
I think I'll be alright!
He did leave all the materials
I need in the laboratory.
I can't make any improvements
to my equipment,
but I can keep them
in working order!
That's good.
[Seryu sighs]
[DR. STYLISH]
So, Seryu, tell me how
Judgement‐of‐the‐Ten‐Kings
and your other new weapons
have been working for you.
Great! I'm really
enjoying them, Doctor!
I'm quite impressed with
how well your body
handled the experiment.
Now use all that newfound power
to make your dreams come true.
And I'll be right here to fix
you if you get a boo boo.
Ha...
Okay!
[SERYU]
My parents...
Captain Ogre...
and the Doctor.
Everyone I care about
gets killed...
and always by the same filth!
[Koro whines]
Seryu.
[SERYU]
Commander... I...
I can't take it anymore!
All I want...
is to slaughter them all
as soon as possible!
[Gasp]
If you'll stay with me, Seryu,
I promise I will
fulfill that wish.
You can count on it.
Thank you!
I swear, Commander...
I will dedicate everything
I have to you, and to justice.
[ESDEATH]
I know you will.
[WAVE]
Here we go!
I'm gonna find Seryu
and put a great big
smile on her face!
And what makes you
so sure you can do that?
It's something my mom
told me one time.
If a girl's ever crying
or acting upset
it's a man's job to make
her feel better again!
[KUROME]
Mm... Hmmm...
[WAVE]
And this is
one of those times.
Seryu, lay your troubles on me!
Ehh... haha...
Uh...
[NAJENDA]
It looks like the Empire
is gradually beginning
to build up its forces.
And there's no way
we can win
as we are now.
We have to make
ourselves stronger.
[Chelsea teasing Mine]
[NAJENDA]
Revolution Day is almost here.
Let's use what little time
we have left for training.
I also wouldn't count on
getting any more new fighters
if I were you.
Please consider this the last
time we receive reinforcements.
If we work as a team,
we can all survive to see
the coming of the new world!
[TATSUMI]
Hm.
[Creaking]
Ah, got one!
Huh?
Much better.
It's gonna be a huge feast
tonight! I can't wait!
[LEONE]
Phew!
Ah man, that was delicious
and hit the spot, Su!
I feel like I can
take on the world!
Thank you for
all your help.
Hey, Su, so you think we could
train together tomorrow?
Hmm. I knew you'd come around
once you saw how handy
he can be.
It is pretty cool that the
guys back at Headquarters
would let you borrow
such an awesome weapon.
[NAJENDA]
They said Susanoo had been in
hibernation for quite some time.
He felt my presence,
and activated immediately.
That's really cool.
Oh, it's easy to see why.
My feminine charm, of course.
Actually the General is
like a spitting image
of my previous master.
That makes sense.
If she was like me,
then she must have been
a wonderful person.
Yeah.
Not only a great leader,
but also a good man!
A man?!
Gah...
Hahaha...
See, Boss, you totally
look like a dude!
That's probably why
you're such a stud!
Cut it out, if you make her
mad she's gonna freak out
and kill us...
Oh! Uh...
Yeah sorry.
[TATSUMI]
Uh‐oh...
[NAJENDA]
Grrr...
[LEONE and TATSUMI]
Oww...
Jeez, I don't get why
everybody's so quick to
cozy up to that guy.
I thought I was the
Mr. Suave Awesome
around here.
Don't worry, Lubb, I'm pretty
sure no one considered you
"suave" in the first place.
[Meow]
[Mine]
Oh, wow.
Is that a baby panther cub?
[Meow]
They're surprisingly
comfortable around
humans, aren't they?
[Meow]
Hey now, I'm not gonna share
my food with you or anything so‐
[Cute meow]
Uhh...
Okay... maybe just one bite.
[Hiss]
Whoa!
Hehehe....
What a PURRfect little snack!
Whaa‐?! It's you?!
Hehehe...
Oh, Mine, you always
make it so easy
I just can't help
myself! Mmm...
I hate you!
‐Grrr...
[LUBBOCK]
‐So that was your Imperial Arms?
It sure was! I can instantly
transform into anything I want!
Pretty cool, right?
Gaia Foundation, it's perfect
for stealth operations.
Which I must say Mine,
if you're not more careful,
you'll be the next
team member to
get killed on
the battlefield.
Excuse me?!
If the enemy finds out
about your weapon,
then you're screwed!
Admittedly. It is a
cosmetic‐type Imperial Arms,
so I can't do any
real damage with it.
‐Grrr...
‐But that's what makes the
art of deception so exciting!
‐Ahh!
‐Like that look of surprise
on your face a minute ago...
Makes it all worth it.
[Chelsea laughs]
[MINE]
AHHH! God I hate you!
[Beasts growls]
[Roars]
Tatsumi, you take care
of the little one!
[TATSUMI]
You got it!
All their attacks do
a lot of damage.
I need to study
their movements...
avoid taking any
direct hits...
and take 'em down!
Uh!
[LEONE]
There it is.
Incursio's hidden polearm,
Neuntote!
I don't know where
it started...
But Tatsumi's really started
to pull his own weight!
Heh!
He'll be right up there with
Bulat one of these days.
Guh!
[Roar]
There's no end to these
ugly little shits!
It's like they keep calling
for backup or something.
The leader's gotta be
around here somewhere.
Hot damn!
Hyaaaa!
[Roars]
Nice try!
I guess that must be
your trump card!
Huh?
Waaah!
Ha! Didn't even break a sweat!
[NAJENDA]
Well done! You've proven
you can easily kill
the Danger Beasts
in this area.
I've noticed some of
the different types
like to attack us
out of nowhere,
so we constantly
have to be on our toes!
I like it! That makes it
so much more interesting!
[NAJENDA]
The air's pretty thin up here.
You've been training in
such a harsh environment...
I'm sure all of you have
leveled up quite a bit!
You're right!
I can already feel
a huge difference!
‐Chelsea.
‐Hm?
Tell me. What do you
think of Night Raid
now that you've been
with us for a month?
Hm. You're all strong.
In fact I would say you're
even stronger than anyone
from my old team.
Ha!
Aw yeah!
You got that right!
That said...
Just because you're strong
doesn't mean you'll survive.
I took the liberty of looking
through all your old reports.
Sheele and Bulat were both
killed in a recent battle.
The issue at hand
isn't whether or not
they were good people.
It's that those two were
obviously incompetent.
Hmm!
What?
[CHELSEA]
All I'm trying to say is
if you don't get it together,
then you're not going to
last long enough
to see this fight
through to the end.
[MINE]
I swear...
That girl pisses me off so much!
Well, that's Chelsea for you;
she's as honest as they come.
We should eat something.
Let's go ahead and get a
head‐start on cooking
everything you hunted.
Can't work on
an empty stomach.
There is something really
wrong with you guys.
[TATSUMI]
So, what did you want to
talk about, Mine?
You know it had to
make you mad.
I can't believe what she said
about Sheele and Bulat!
[TATSUMI]
Yeah, I understand.
I don't like it when
people disrespect Bro.
We need to do something to her
that'll really screw her up.
Something that'll scare the
crap out of her or at least
make her look stupid.
Here it is. You get her off
her guard, really shake her up,
then I'll come in and
deal the final blow!
It's total genius!
Why do I feel like nothing
good can possibly come
from teaming up with you?
What do you mean?!
Don't you dare tell me
that you're gonna take
her side on this one?
You know she deserves it!
Okay, okay, fine,
whatever you want.
But wait, you never explained
how you wanted me to
surprise Chelsea.
Well, you and Lubb will have to
figure something out, won't you?
I've got my own brilliant
revenge to prepare.
So get busy, this mission
should be completed tonight!
And I'd better hear
her scream too!
[LUBBOCK]
I don't think I like her tone.
[TATSUMI]
Hmm... Something that'll
make Chelsea scream...
I got nothin' over here.
If only we could use our
Imperial Arms to startle people‐
OH! I think I just
had an idea!
And it was a GOOD idea!
Whoaaa!
[TATSUMI]
Never thought I'd use
Incursio for this.
Listen up! It's almost time
for Chelsea to take a bath,
so make sure you're ready!
You just need to go invisible
and sneak into the hot spring
from the back.
As soon as you can
get close enough...
all you have to do is
grab the wash bucket and
dump it over her head!
She's totally gonna freak out,
it'll be great! I promise.
[TATSUMI]
Hmm...
Are you sure this
is a good idea?
Come on! Mine's practically
forcing us to do it,
so we have the
perfect excuse!
It's a once‐in‐a‐lifetime
chance!
Well, okay...
But I can't let you
come with me.
You understand,
right, Lubb?
Hm... That's cool!
I'll let you have
the fun part!
You're the best!
[LUBBOCK]
This is perfect!
Now I can gauge how mad Chelsea
will get at a peeping tom
without having to get
my own ass beat.
If she lets him
off the hook,
maybe I can get away
with it too!
[TATSUMI]
I should just get this
over with.
Otherwise I could spend
the whole night just
staring at her.
Okay. Maybe for a second.
[Deep breath]
Alright, let's do this.
Uh...
Ahhh! That's DEFINITELY a guy!
[SUSANOO]
You can come out now.
I know you're there.
[TATSUMI]
Uh!
Su?! How'd you know?!
[SUSANOO]
Incursio can make you invisible,
but that's all it does.
You'll have to learn to hide
your aura on your own.
[TATSUMI]
Huh!
Always bear that in mind
when you fight.
If you forget, it's over.
[TATSUMI]
Uh‐huh.
Huh.
[CHELSEA]
You left yourself open!
Huh?! Wha... What?!
Haha...
Surprise ya?
It was me the whole time!
Ahh...
Uh, you seriously need
to work on
quelling that aura
of yours, Tatsumi.
The moment I sensed it, I knew
I could turn the tables on you.
Oh yeah, I guess that's
why you were sitting here
waiting for me then, huh?
You win this round!
[CHELSEA]
Hehe... Deception is my
specialty, you know.
To detect something like that
you'd need much more training.
I'm sorry, does it get on your
nerves when people tell you
things like that?
Not really.
Hm?
I understand what
you're saying, Chelsea.
There's still so many things
I need to improve.
I promise I'll take
your advice to heart.
[CHELSEA]
So, you're pretty
mature, aren't you?
The truth is...
Not too long ago
I came back from a mission
only to discover that
everyone on my team
had been murdered
while I was gone.
I would be devastated
if something like that
were to happen to
the people here.
All I'm trying to say is
if you don't get it together
then you're not going to
last long enough to see
this fight through to the end.
[TATSUMI]
The only reason she
said all that stuff
was because she was
concerned about us.
Hmm...
How about that?
You're a lot sweeter than
I thought you were
when we first met.
[CHELSEA]
Uhmm...
How dare you say that to me!
Just looking out for my mental
well‐being like anybody would!
And the next time you try to
sneak a little peek at me
when I'm naked...
I won't hesitate to
cut it off, is that clear?
Uh... did you say "cut it off"?!
Cut WHAT off?!
[Street chatter]
[ESDEATH]
Uh...
Hmm, Commander?
Yeah?
Is there anything troubling you?
Whenever there's a large crowd,
I find myself searching
for Tatsumi.
[RUN]
Actually...
If I may... I've compiled
a list of eligible bachelors
who all bear some
resemblance to that boy.
If it pleases you, I could
set up some meetings.
[ESDEATH]
There's no need to
trouble yourself, Run.
There can only be one
Tatsumi, after all.
No one else will ever
come close.
[RUN]
My humblest apologies.
Hmm, this complicates things.
I knew she was sadistic
and that she's tasked with
the Minister's dirty work.
But she's even more powerful
and depraved than I imagined.
It should prove rather
entertaining to observe her
up close for a little while.
[ESDEATH]
Why do I feel so anxious?
Am I sensing that I'm about
to see Tatsumi again?
Or is it because...
because the final battle
against Night Raid is
drawing near.
Or perhaps, it's something
else altogether!
[Grunting]
Uh...
[Roar]
[MINER]
Ahh! It's some new kind
of Danger Beast!
[OTHER MINER]
RUN!
Ahh!
[SYURA]
Hehehe...
Looks like I got my hands
on a fun little new toy!
Y'know, I haven't been to
the Capital in ages...
Should be a wonderful time.
[Music playing]