[TATSUMI]
I wanted... to spend more
time with everyone.
I wish we could've kept
fighting together.
If only I was...
I don't know...
[MINE]
Hey, Tatsumi, you
gonna sleep all day?
Oh!
No, I'm up!
Sorry you guys, I overslept.
It's time to infiltrate the
Path of Peace headquarters.
Get it together!
[TATSUMI]
Yeah yeah, I know!
And after we clean out
the filth in Kyoroku,
that's when the Revolutionary
Army will make its move, right?
There's no time to dwell
on the past right now.
I have to overthrow this
disgusting Empire.
This madness must be
stopped at the source!
[Crowd chatter]
[ESDEATH]
Counselor Bolic.
Via direct orders from
Minister Honest,
the Jaegers Special Police force
is here to ensure your safety.
[BOLIC]
My my.
Who would've guessed he'd send
the one and only all‐powerful
General Esdeath of all people
to look after this great estate?
I must tell you I've never
felt safer in my life.
[ESDEATH]
We've received a report
stating that Night Raid
is already in the city.
We'll need to use your guest
rooms until the hunt is over.
It's my pleasure.
Heh, I think you'll find our
hospitality quite satisfying.
I have no interest in
playing with your pets.
But, as for those spies
watching my team since
we walked in...
I'd love to meet them.
[BOLIC]
Ooh, well played.
I should've expected
you'd notice.
[WAVE]
Who are those guys?
[BOLIC]
I borrowed these highly
disturbed individuals
from the Imperial Fist Temple
to keep this religion
under my control.
Say hello to the
Four Rakshasa Demons!
Oh! So that's why I hadn't
seen them in the Capital;
I wondered where they went.
[BOLIC]
It actually works out nicely,
they usually work
as my bodyguards,
but since you're here, I can
put them on the offensive
and let them handle those
assassins for you.
Wait a second!
How can they go against Night
Raid without Imperial Arms‐
Oh don't worry your
pretty little head!
Taking out Imperial Arms
users just happens to be
our specialty.
It's what I live for... [slurp]
No matter how unbeatable an
Imperial Arms might seem...
...you can't escape the fact
the wielder's only flesh and
blood underneath.
So like, there's a million
different ways to defeat
one, y'know?
These four just happen
to be the Minister's
personal executioners.
And as their name implies,
they're good at it.
He ain't lyin'.
We can handle this.
So just sit back, relax,
have a few cocktails and‐
While it may be true
that you've built up
an impressive résumé...
you shouldn't let
your guard down.
Ooh, so sinister.
You're giving me chills,
General Esdeath.
I think I'm falling for you.
That's strange...
if the Minister's favorite
pawns already had it
under control,
why did he choose to send us?
This religious group must
mean a lot more to him
than I thought.
[Kurome breathing rapidly]
[WAVE]
Kurome!
Please no...
If only I'd gotten here
a little sooner...
Maybe Bols would
still be alive...
And and what about his
wife and his daughter?
God how in the hell am I
supposed to report this?!
I don't know...
but the reason you were
attacked was because
you were trying to save
Kurome, right?
That's why the Commander said
you wouldn't be held
responsible for what happened.
I understand how you feel,
but please stay calm.
[Wave crying]
[WAVE]
Damn it...
DAMN IT!
[ESDEATH]
How's Kurome?
She's still sleeping.
But the doctor believes
she's healed enough
that she can
recover soon.
That's good.
I'm trying to identify
the body of the girl who
attacked her, but I'm
coming up short.
[WAVE]
She was probably
one of Night Raid's
Imperial Arms users.
[ESDEATH]
I agree.
Commander?
Is it okay if I feed that
evil lady's remains to Koro?
[ESDEATH]
Sure, why not?
Haa!
Time to get up!
Ah!
[WAVE]
K‐Kurome!
I feel a lot better.
Now that I've had
a little nap.
[WAVE]
What? You're kidding me!
But your wounds...
they were... fatal.
[KUROME]
Commander!
If it pleases you, I'd like to
continue with my mission now.
As you can see,
I'm ready to fight!
[ESDEATH]
That's fine.
But if you're coming with us,
you can't fall behind.
In thirty minutes we're
leaving with or without you.
Right!
[RUN]
Wave? Is something wrong?
Huh? Uh, no!
[Labored breathing]
[WAVE]
Hey, you okay in there?
You're not feeling
better at all, are you?
I'm really thinking you
need to sit this mission out.
[KUROME]
No! I'm fine.
[WAVE]
How can you say that?
I'm gonna let the Commander
know you're not ready for‐
Ah...
Uhh...
Kurome!
In my old squad,
if they find out you
can't fight anymore...
they simply killed you to be
sure that you'd never talk!
What?
Kill you?
If I get kicked out
of the Jaegers...
I might...
You'll be okay!
If you tell the Commander,
she'll protect you!
She can't help me
with this!
The only way is
to keep fighting.
I won't allow myself
to be discarded.
I didn't come into this terrible
world to go out like that!
If anyone kills me,
it will be in battle.
Just like my friends who
died when we were kids.
Kurome.
Sorry I made you
worry, Wave.
I really am alright.
Just let me recover
a little more;
and I should be back to
my old self again.
Hmm...
[TATSUMI]
Good news is ‐ we're pretty
far away from the Capital,
so we probably don't need
to worry about wanted
posters, do we?
We can't be sure the Jaegers
haven't been going around
posting new ones.
Let's try to be caref‐
Are you frickin' serious,
you couldn't even let me get
the words out of my mouth?!
Look I understand
what you're saying.
Hm...
Oh...
But isn't there such a thing
as being too careful?
The enemy might notice if
we start acting all jumpy.
So we have to be natural.
[MINE]
He was crushed when
Chelsea died...
but now here he is, taking the
assignment with a brave face.
Hmph! He's growing up.
Whatever, I guess you
do kinda have a point.
Oh!
Wow, this is really good!
Yep! You can't get
ice cream this good
just anywhere.
[TATSUMI]
Speaking of which,
have you noticed how much busier
it is here than the city?
[MINE]
Thanks to their underground
resources and that religion.
Religion?
Yeah, it's big bucks.
But the way they've got it
set up right now,
the vast majority of the
profits go straight to
the Minister's wallet.
That pig.
These people have no idea
they're being taken.
[MINE]
Everyone in the resistance
knows the truth,
but Bolic keeps their hands
pretty much tied.
That's why we're
gonna teach that
bastard a lesson.
Yep. But we can't do anything
until we figure out our way
around town, right?
[TATSUMI]
Oh yeah!
Let's see what's
outside the city next!
Sounds good.
Since Lubb was all
gung‐ho about it,
we'll let him handle the danger
zone around the cathedral.
[Drinking]
[LUBBOCK]
Jeez! This place is
like a maze.
Well, at least it's fairly easy
to get lost in the crowd
and feel things out.
Oops, careful.
Luckily the Empire doesn't
know my face or my name.
And the more info I bring back
the more points I can
score with Najenda!
You've made me so happy...
Hehaheha...
[MEZ]
Hey, Shuten.
That guy down there
totally looks like
he's sniffing around.
My intuition tells me,
he's got to be an
enemy for sure.
The way he's moving
is a dead giveaway.
The guy carries himself
as if he's already seen
a lot of action.
He probably thinks he's
being pretty cautious,
but he can't hide it from me.
Meaning he's guilty!
Are you ready to kill him then?
Don't call it that. Please.
I like to think of it as
'freeing his spirit.'
[SPY]
Based on our observations,
we believe there's an
underground path near
this cemetery
that passes through Bolic's
mansion to the cathedral.
So if we found the entrance
to the tunnel...
we could easily slip into
Bolic's basement.
It'll take a while
to find it.
Since there is quite
a lot of land to cover.
[AKAME]
Hmm...
We should also bear in mind
that it might be full of traps.
[Slice sound]
[IBARA]
Hehe...
Well, well, well.
Did you think no one would
notice you were here, Akame?
[AKAME]
Ibara. So you're in Kyoroku too.
[IBARA]
Oh, you mean you remember me?
I'm touched.
It's not like we really
knew each other back on
the assassination squad.
I knew we'd see the
Four Rakshasa Demons
by going for the Minister...
but I wasn't expecting this
until the final battle.
Hehe... Such a naughty girl
for betraying the Empire...
I'm kinda honored to be
the one to punish you!
I don't think so!
Oh, really!
Ha!
Haa!
[IBARA]
Haha...
On top of all our training,
we were given another
little advantage!
We drank a special broth made
from mountain Lake‐Krakens
living near the temple.
It lets me do some 'unusual'
things with my body!
Crap! He just came at me
out of nowhere!
How did I blow my cover?!
[SHUTEN]
Hehe... Come back and fight
like a man, you coward?
Uh‐oh, you dead already?
Well hell you're no fun.
[LUBBOCK]
Come on, get outta here.
My string armor
blocked that attack,
but I managed to stop my
pulse by using Cross Tail
around my blood vessels.
It's not very comfortable,
so you can be on your
way now, alright?
In the end, you were just
an insignificant little pest
not even worth my time.
Ah, well.
[LUBBOCK]
That's it, walk away.
I'm getting a little tired of
playing dead in the street.
Hey Shuten there's another one
headed your way.
And it looks like she's a
revolutionary spy too.
Uh‐oh...
I bet that's the girl I was
supposed to meet up with.
Sorry babe, you're on your own.
Well, if she's a spy
she should be prepared
for stuff like this.
[Girl panicking]
Well now, another poor lamb
lost in this frightening world.
I'd be happy to help you out
and free your spirit for you,
you should be thanking me!
Ah! Please let me go...
[Crying]
Hehe...
[Grunt]
Nope, I can't do it!
I won't let you kill an ally,
especially a cutie like that.
But I checked you,
you didn't have a pulse.
That was dumb!
If you had stayed still we
would've had like no idea!
Here's the thing.
Because of the role
I play on the team...
I usually avoid as many head‐on
confrontations as possible.
But...
When push comes to shove,
I don't play around.
And I don't hold back!
I'll kick both of your asses
at the same time!
[IBARA]
Hahaha!
That is one freaky
weapon of yours!
Murasame is the perfect sword
for damaged goods like you!
C'mon, c'mon, I know you
can move faster than
that little lady!
It's too bad you left before
completing your training!
Thanks! I'll be taking that!
Hehe...
Huh? What the hell's
wrong with this thing?!
Huh? Ah!
Don't tell me...
you planned all this
from the beginning
and actually let me take
your weapon from you!
The answer was clear as
soon as you couldn't
understand Murasame.
There was no way it
would bond with you.
Arrrgh, damn you!
You little bitch!
Looks like my cursed blade
didn't take a liking to you.
[AKAME]
It may have something to do
with your winning personality.
[IBARA]
Heh. You're a pretty
messed up chick, aren't you?
Careful, I think I might be
falling in love.
I'm kinda into
that sorta thing...
Ugh...
[RUN]
Surprise attacks don't
work on you, I see.
A Jaeger I presume.
Yes.
Now I know Akame of
Night Raid is in the city.
Handling recon is my job.
I was watching you fight...
so I've just learned a
great deal about Murasame.
The Four Demons AND the Jaegers.
I hope everyone's okay.
Well? Come at me!
Yeah I don't think so!
That string will slice me to
pieces if I get too close to it.
Oh, I guess you noticed.
I'm gonna free your spirit
like I should've done before.
Fist Temple...
Hundred Fists! Aah!
Thanks, but I didn't
ask for that!
Whoa. You're very good
with your hands.
I guess that thread
is your Imperial Arms.
[MEZ]
[Cracks knuckles]
If it is, then that makes you
a member of Night Raid.
This time I'll split your
head open to be totally
positive you're dead.
Sorry, you're cute and all; but
I'm not into that kinda thing!
Hm...
[LUBBOCK]
Strings, bind together!
Now... centrifugal force!
That was stupid.
You left yourself wide open!
Yeah, but it's no big deal.
Watch this!
Ultimate move: Wire Impact!
Aaah!
Is that all you got?
If this is your trump card, it's
the saddest one I've ever seen.
[LUBBOCK]
Oh, you think so?
Well if you haven't noticed,
it just let me accomplish
exactly what I wanted.
Take a look behind you.
Hm?
Uh, wait...
Aw crap.
See ya later, suckers!
Whoo!
That whole time he was
creating a diversion
so we wouldn't notice that
the other one was getting away.
I'm an idiot.
Well if nothing else,
I can at least chase you
down now can't I?!
You sure it's a such good idea
to come after me like that?
[LUBBOCK]
My string is made from the
fur of an S‐Class Danger Beast
that hails from the high clouds
over the Eastern Sea.
The fibers protect its
vital organs, and they're
ridiculously strong.
These incredible, resilient
strands are razor‐sharp,
and lovingly known as
"World Severing String."
I'm coming!
They have never let me down.
There's no way you
can cut through it.
Ahh!
You're finished!
It's gonna take more than that.
My body has had
decades of training.
I won't die from this!
In a few seconds it won't matter
how strong your body is.
Cross Tail's already finding
its way around inside you,
and once it wraps around
your heart it's over.
Hmm?
[Heart beating]
Ugh!
Never thought much about
training your guts, did ya?
[MEZ]
Ooh, that was cool!
Huh?
You just killed Shuten.
The Minister's gonna
yell at me for like ever.
[LUBBOCK]
Nah, you won't have to
worry about that.
Sorry about this.
But you've seen my weapon,
so there's no way
I can let you live.
Aw, don't be sorry!
I'm an assassin too;
I totally get it.
[Clank]
Arrrh...
Huh?!
What's all that liquid?
Crap! It's weighing down
my strings,
the barrier's ruined!
It's my body oil,
more like sweat really.
The Rakshasa Demons are
experts at doing weird stuff
with our bodies.
So yeah, that's what happened
to your little web thingy.
Whoa! She's fast!
Uh, uh, ah!
Hehe...
Ugh, I can't move...
If I take one more hit...
I'm a dead man.
Uhh...
Hiya!
[MEZ]
Oh don't do that,
it's so desperate.
[LUBBOCK]
[Coughing]
Damn, you sure are pretty.
If things were different,
I'd totally ask you out.
Hehe... And you're just
the kinda guy I like,
so I probably would've
been interested.
Hehe...
[MEZ]
But oh well!
Maybe in another life.
Good night.
[Stabbing sound]
Uh...
Uuuh...
[LUBBOCK]
I kinda used my strings
to grab those knives
from earlier.
And then I just bided my time
for the right moment
to rewind it back in and well,
you know the rest.
[Stabbed]
Ugh!
Sorry.
Guess I should get outta here.
Hm...
Aw, man, it's not fair!
The one time a girl
actually likes me!
[Tatsumi sighs]
We covered a lot of
ground today,
but we still need to check
all the backstreets and
byroads and everything else.
[MINE]
This city's way too big!
Yeah but isn't that why
we're searching it?
[sigh]
This would be a heck of
a lot more fun
if we included
some shopping.
[TATSUMI]
Maybe for you.
It's a nightmare to be the one
following you around.
[MINE]
Err! You got a problem with it?
If a man can't appreciate
a lady's retail needs,
he has poor character.
And I think women who
come up with stupid reasons
for calling a
man's character poor
have poor character,
how 'bout that?
Now you're asking for it!
Do I need to remind you
who's in charge here?
You need to remember
your place!
Jeez, when are you gonna
get it through your head?
You're not in charge of me;
we're the same rank!
Grrrr...
[LORD]
Please, cease this
foundless quarreling.
Huh?
Who are you?
[LORD]
Apologies.
I know it's none
of my business...
but I simply could
not help but intervene.
[MINE]
By any chance are you with...
[TATSUMI]
...the Path of Peace.
I am.
In sooth I'm the Founding Lord;
on occasion I make
a sojourn to the city.
I have had a vision.
I see you two joined by
the red string of fate.
Cast off your differences
and confess your love!
Huh?
Upon forming your bond..
the occasional healthy
disagreement can be
quite beneficial!
Huh?
[TATSUMI / MINE]
Whaaat?!
[MINE]
I would never marry
a jerk like him?!
[TATSUMI]
Oh yeah, like you're
a trophy wife!
[LORD] You truly are made
for one another.
[MINE]
Oh you're one to talk.
[BOLIC]
Good news, dear.
I'm bestowing upon you
the coveted honor
of serving as the
Lord's assistant.
Oh! Really?
I'm so happy I get
to see the Lord
performing his
miracles up close!
This is a dream
come true!
[BOLIC]
However, you still haven't
completely cleansed your
mind of evil thoughts.
You're not yet fit
for the task.
O‐oh no!
Not to worry, child;
simply remove your clothes
and I will purify you
with a sacred ritual.
Yes, Counselor Bolic.
Please help me.
Soon this religion
will be under my thumb.
I'm going to enjoy
this very much.
[MONK]
Conselor Bolic!
[BOLIC]
What is it?
I'm in the middle
of a ceremony!
It's the Four Demons.
Uh...
[RUN]
It seems three of them were
eliminated in one night.
They underestimated Night Raid.
I knew it from the start;
we're the only ones capable of
crushing those nasty sinners
beneath the mighty
Hammer of Justice!
Najenda, I fell for your
tricks on the way here,
but I'll turn this place
into a slaughter house.
For you and your team.
[Music playing]