[explosion]
Whoa!
[rumbling growl]
[MERCHANT]
It's an Earth Dragon!
[deep roar]
[horrified screams]
[TATSUMI]
Class One Danger Beast... Right.
An Earth Dragon.
This should be fun.
[rumbling growl]
Aah, don't be mad.
I'll take care of ya!
[MERCHANT]
That was incredible, kid!
You took down a Class One
Danger Beast all by yourself!
Aww, it was nothing!
Kinda like taking candy
from a big, scaly baby!
...uhh...
Oh yeah, and the name's
Tatsumi by the way.
The whole capital's gonna know
my name before too long,
so you might wanna remember it.
[MERCHANT 1]
So you're going to the Imperial
Capital to seek your fortune?
Yep! Where I come from,
everyone dreams of making
it big in the capital.
[MERCHANT]
Look kid, the Imperial Capital
isn't some perfect dreamland.
Sure it's the big city,
but it's been overrun
with monsters even more vicious
than this Earth Dragon here.
[TATSUMI] I don't get it;
how can the city be full
of Danger Beasts?
Not those monsters.
They're humans,
but with the hearts of monsters.
Damn place is
crawling with them.
[TATSUMI]
Thanks for the warning, guys,
but there's no way I'm gonna
turn around and go back now.
You see, me and my friends,
we have a mission:
to make a fortune,
and save our village!
[NARRATOR] All people must
one day turn to ash,
so too must nations
fall to ruin.
Despite the capital's wealth
and prosperity,
it has become mired
in corruption.
The pompous, and the vile,
run rampant
throughout the city.
These demons are
beyond salvation.
And are therefore silenced
in the darkness
by an elite group of assassins.
[music playing]
Oooh maaan...
The capital's even bigger
than I thought!
If things work out here,
I can just BUY the village!
All right, I better get
to the barracks.
[RECEPTIONIST] So you'd
like to enlist, would ya?
All right, just fill out the
form and bring it back to me.
[TATSUMI]
Wait, wait, wait, wait...
This says I'd be
starting as a private.
You think you're special?
[TATSUMI]
Not starting from the bottom!
I'm way too good for that.
I was thinking something
more along the lines of a,
say, captain!
[RECEPTIONIST] Get the hell
outta here!
[TATSUMI] WAAHHH!
Hey, c'mon, can I at
least take the test?!
There's a depression going on!
I already got more applicants
than I can handle!
I'm not gonna waste a spot
on some stupid kid!
Huh? A depression?
[RECEPTIONIST]
Now get outta here! Beat it!
[sighs]
Maybe I could stage
like a kidnapping
and save the day just in time...
Nah, that's too obvious.
[LEONE] Hellooooo!
[TATSUMI] Hmmm?
[LEONE] What's with the long
face there, little guy?
It'll be all right, Big Sis is
here to cheer you up!
[TATSUMI] Aaaahhhh...
I think I love this place!
[LEONE] Hm?
Try to focus here, buddy.
[TATSUMI] Ahhhhh...
So, let me guess!
You came in from the countryside
in search of fame and fortune,
didn't you?
[TATSUMI] How'd you know that?!
I've lived here for a long time.
By now, it's super easy
to spot a new face.
Hey! I know the secret to
becoming an officer in
the army super quick.
Tell me!
[LEONE] You really wanna know?
Ahuh, ahuh.
Well... first you gotta
treat me to lunch.
[gulp, gulp]
Man! Never too early in the day
for some hooch, am I right?!
(belch)
Go ahead, drink up! There's
still a little more left.
Look just forget the drinks
and tell me how to become
an officer!
[LEONE]
Yeah... well, about that, uh...
First you're gonna need
a lot of money.
Money?
[LEONE] Ya' see I...
just happen to know
someone in the army.
He could hook you up
if you make it worth his while.
Okay then.
Let's see...
Will this be enough?
Whoo! Whadda we have here?!
It's just some reward money
from killing a Class One
Danger Beast, no biggy.
Hmmm?
Big guy...
You might just jump
straight up to captain!
Yeah? Let's hope so!
I believe our little
encounter's been educational
in more ways than you know, kid.
Right, I'm gonna talk to him.
You wait here, okay?
Seee yaaa!
[music playing]
Hey buddy, I'd like to go home
sometime tonight, ya know.
Oh, I'm just waiting here
for somebody.
Yeah, sorry to tell
you this son,
but she took your money and ran.
Huh?
HUH?!
Don't you know better than
to just hand some stranger
everything you got?
I gotta go find her!
Which way did she go?!
[BARTENDER]
Don't waste your time.
It's your own fault
you got scammed.
Aaaaaaaa...
[TATSUMI]
Aaww, this totally sucks!
That was every penny I had!
Damn that rack!
No wait,
better yet damn that girl!
I guess that was
my "educational experience".
[LEONE] (evil cackle)
(grrrrr)
Awww...
None of the people back at the
village are such liars.
Guess...
I'm sleeping outside.
Don't really have
a choice, do I?
[ARIA] (gasp) Stop right here!
[GAURRY] Are we really
doing this again, milady?
[ARIA] You know I can't help it!
This is just the way I am.
[ARIA] Excuse me.
Um, if you need someplace to
rest your head tonight,
you're welcome to
come home with me?
Uh... thanks, but I'm broke.
[ARIA](giggle)
Well if you weren't, you
wouldn't be here, now would you?
Lady Aria has a bit of a
weakness for helping
those with nowhere to go.
[BODYGUARD] You really
should accept her offer.
Pretty please.
Well, uh,
it's better than sleeping out
on the street I guess.
Great, let's go home!
[FATHER] Oh! Looks like Aria
brought home another guest.
[MOTHER]
Oh my! So it would seem.
How many does this make?
[ARIA] Mother!
Uh... oh!
Thank you so much for having me.
[TATSUMI]
Those guys are really big.
[FATHER] (laughs)
Don't be so nervous, young man!
[TATSUMI] Must make it easier
[MOTHER]
Would you like something to eat?
to let complete strangers
stay at your house
with security like that.
You can feel pretty safe.
And just when I thought
everyone in the capital
[Heavenly chorus]
were all a bunch of
evil scumbags!
[TATSUMI] I really
appreciate all of this!
So your plan is...
to make a name for yourself
in the Imperial Capital.
Is that correct?
Right!
[FATHER] As you may know,
the capital is a wonderful
and peaceful place.
However, it is bordered
by squabbling tribes
on three sides.
If you are to enlist,
you may be expected to go
and join the fight.
I'm prepared for that.
Yes, I'm sure you are!
Seems you've got spirit.
I like to see that
in a young man.
Did you come all the way here
by yourself, Tatsumi?
[TATSUMI] No, I'm not alone.
There's three of us.
[TATSUMI] We're gonna hit
the road now, Mayor!
[MAYOR] Well, you three have
been pushing each other
since you were just children.
It's time to use that energy
to make something good
of yourselves.
You can count on us, sir!
We'll bring fortune
back to the village.
That's right, nobody's
gonna starve on our watch!
Give it about ten years or so,
and everybody for miles
around'll know the name Ieyasu!
Sure, as long as you
don't get arrested
and have your head
chopped off before then.
Jeez, Sayo, do you always
have to be so morbid?!
[MAYOR]
They're as spirited as always.
[SAYO] At least I have
a sense of direction,
[SAYO]
you should try working on that!
Oh and Tatsumi,
I have something for you.
[IEYASU] Maybe you should try
shuttin' your big dumb face!
[MAYOR] It's a parting gift.
If times get tough...
I'll sell it.
[MAYOR] The hell you will!
[MAYOR] Look just keep it
on you at all times.
It ensures God will protect you.
[TATSUMI] Okay...
Thank you very much!
[TATSUMI] At first, it
seemed like everything was
going pretty smoothly.
But then we got attacked
by bandits, and well...
We lost each other.
Ooh...
Both of them are
decent fighters at least,
so I'm not TOO concerned.
It's just that Ieyasu still
can't navigate his way
out of a paper bag.
What was that?!
We planned to meet each other
at the capital,
but I don't think
he's gonna make it.
[FATHER] Then it's settled.
[TATSUMI](huh?)
I think I have a friend in the
military who can help you.
I'll give him your name,
and ask him to look for
your two friends.
That'd be great!
Again thank you so much!
I have an extremely
keen intuition.
So I just know you'll see
your friends again very soon.
That'd be great.
I've been so lucky...
I ended up finding some great
people to look out for me.
Now there's just
Sayo and Ieyasu.
I hope they found their way
to the capital safe and sound.
[ARIA] Oh! We should go
to that shop next!
[BODYGUARD] Please wait, milady!
Whoa, Lady Aria's a pretty
serious shopper, isn't she?
I mean, I don't think I've ever
seen so much stuff before.
The young lady does enjoy it,
but I assume all women
behave this way, yes?
I don't know.
I have this other female friend
and she just kinda wears
whatever she has.
That's because I'm poor,
you jerk!
Oh, and Tatsumi...
[TATSUMI] Yeah?
You see the castle over there?
[TATSUMI] Huh?
That is the center of
the entire empire.
It's where everything happens.
[TATSUMI] Whoa!
I've always wanted to see
where the emperor lives
and makes decisions
for the whole country!
Well... not exactly.
Uh...
There is an emperor,
but he's only a child.
Our land is plagued
by corruption.
It's the minister who controls
the emperor from the shadows.
[TATSUMI] Minister‐!
[GAURRY]
Do not let yourself be heard.
Those who oppose are beheaded.
So... he's the one who ordered
all those heavy taxes
on my village.
[GAURRY]
The entire capital knows.
(grrr...)
On top of that,
we're dealing with this scum.
[TATSUMI] Night Raid?
[GAURRY] A band of assassins
terrorizing the area.
As the name implies,
they tend to attack at night.
High‐ranking officials
and the upper class
make up most of their targets.
It's only wise
to be very cautious.
Right!
But for the time being...
let's do something about THAT.
What'm I s'posed to do?!
Well, well. Now I can add
another entry to my diary.
What an addicting
little hobby this is!
[swish]
Ah...
[splat]
I'm sorry.
Huh?!
What was that?
Trouble.
There's no way...
[TATSUMI] It's them.
It's Night Raid.
[TATSUMI] What do they want?
I can only assume they've
targeted this family
because they're rich.
What do I do?
Help the guards fight,
or protect the family?
Hey, Akame, those three
guards are targets too.
I'll take care of it.
[BODYGUARDS] Woah!
[GAURRY]
Do not let that sword touch you.
(growls) Let's go!
I knew of the corruption,
yet could not escape it's grasp.
Who the hell are these
monsters?! No!
(gunshot)
[MINE] Not much of a bodyguard,
if he's gonna just run away.
Yeah? I think anyone would
probably run from that.
[TATSUMI] They were wiped out...
in seconds...
I have to save Miss Aria!
[FATHER] (choking)
Please, spare me!
Please, I have a little girl.
[LEONE] It's okay.
You won't for much longer.
No, please don't kill her.
I beg you, have mercy on us!
[LEONE] "Mercy"?
I'm not sure I'm
familiar with that word.
[FATHER](choking)
[BODYGUARD]
Hurry, Milady, this way!
[ARIA] (frantic running)
[ARIA] What's happening?!
[BODYGUARD]
Just get to the shed for now,
you'll be safe there!
[TATSUMI] There you are!
(panting)
[ARIA] Tatsumi?
[BODYGUARD]
Okay, great, you made it.
I'll hide the young lady
and wait for the guards.
See what you can do to stall
the enemy until then.
Got it?
You really expect me
to take out‐
Well... Looks like it's
too late to complain!
[AKAME] You're not a target.
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
[BODYGUARD] Dammit!
(gunfire)
[AKAME] But you are.
[AKAME] You're done.
(small scream)
You deserve this.
[TATSUMI] Stop right there!
I told you, you're not a target.
You don't have to die.
Yeah? Well, I can't let you
murder a helpless little girl.
[AKAME] Mm‐hm.
[TATSUMI] Uh...
[AKAME] So you won't step aside?
Well, I'm not gonna
back down now!
[AKAME] Hmmph.
Then you've made your choice.
[LEONE] Ahhh, that was easy!
(huh?)
That's weird.
It's not like Akame
to take this long.
Wait, what?!
Ah, jeez.
That poor guy can't
catch a break can he?
[TATSUMI] She's better than me.
I don't stand a chance
against her.
But I don't have time
to worry about that.
If I can't save one girl,
how can I possibly expect
to save my entire village?
What the‐ (ugh)
(gasp) Tatsumi!
[TATSUMI] Why'd you
back off all of a sudden?
Because it felt like
I hit some kind of armor.
[TATSUMI] (laughs)
I guess the villagers were
looking out for me after all.
Well now...
He's lasted quite a while
in a fight against Akame.
He must be pretty decent.
She must die.
Hey, wait a minute, lady,
you just said you wanted
to steal this girl's money,
don't you?!
You don't have to kill her!
This isn't a war; there's no
reason to kill innocent people!
Please!
I don't think
she's listening to me.
[AKAME] (huh?)
What are you doing?
We've got some time left.
And I kinda owe
this guy a favor.
I'm pretty sure
he'd like to cash it in now.
(yells)
Hey, you're that girl
with the boobs!
(giggles)
Yep, that's what they call me!
(snarls)
[LEONE] Listen, earlier
you were concerned
we were here to kill
innocent people.
I think you might
see things differently
when you find out
what's behind that door.
(BAMMM!)
Here it is.
Welcome to the capital, kid.
[TATSUMI] What... is all this?
[LEONE]
We learned that they fancied
picking up out‐of‐town
newcomers from the countryside,
and then torture them to death
for their own sick, twisted
entertainment.
That's the reality of this
"poor, innocent, HAPPY
little family".
[TATSUMI] (gasps)
Sayo...
No... that's... that's Sayo...
Do you know who that girl is?
[LEONE] Oopsy!
You didn't really think we were
through with you yet,
did you, sweetie pie?
[TATSUMI]
These people really did this?
Yes, they did, and their guards
are just as guilty
for keeping it hidden.
She's lying!
I had no idea anything
like that was going on!
Who would you believe?
These... these murderers,
or the one who saved you?!
[IEYASU] Tatsumi?
Is that... Is it you?
It's me...
[TATSUMI] Ieyasu?!
[IEYASU] She invited us
to stay at her house.
She gave us something to eat,
and then everything went black.
Then we woke up here...
And... and then that girl...
That GIRL tortured
Sayo to death! (sobs)
Fine, fine so I did it, okay?!
These trash are
just worthless filth.
They're nothing but, but...
livestock for me
to use as I see fit!
Garbage like her doesn't
have the right to such
beautiful hair.
Mine is always
giving me trouble,
so I treated her EXTRA special!
She should be honored that I
gave her so much attention!
Ungrateful PIG!
(hysterical breathing)
Sorry honey, I don't mean
to interrupt your
little tantrum here.
But you are kind of disturbing.
I'll kill her.
[TATSUMI] Wait.
You're kidding? You're still
going to defend her?
[TATSUMI] No.
(swish) I'LL do it!
Hmm... Well, that was quick.
He didn't even hesitate.
Granted,
she was pretty heinous.
[IEYASU]
(chuckles) Thank you, Tatsumi...
I needed to see that...
(coughs up blood)
Ieyasu!
(groaning)
No...
[AKAME] It's the Lebola virus.
The mother enjoyed poisoning
people with different medicines.
She even kept a diary detailing
each victim's reactions.
It's too late for him.
[IEYASU] Tatsumi...
Ieyasu!
You should know...
that Sayo never did break...
She never let herself give in...
She was incredible...
So, I wanted to...
to go out a hero...
His strong will was the only
thing that kept him alive.
(fighting tears) What the hell
is wrong with this place?!
Let's go.
Hey.
Don't you think we should
bring him with us?
Hmm?
[LEONE] We could use
an extra pair of hands.
[TATSUMI](gurk) (struggles)
Plus he seems to have potential
and a little luck on his side.
[TATSUMI]
Wait! I need to bury my friends!
Oh, if you want,
I can take the bodies
[TATSUMI] (struggles)
back to the hideout later, okay?
Just relax!
[TATSUMI] I told you,
I need to bury my frineds!
You're late!
What took you so long?
[TATSUMI] (struggles)
And who's this guy?
A new recruit!
HUH?
[LEONE] Oh, yeah,
I forgot to tell you.
[LEONE] Starting today,
you're part of the team!
Congratulations,
you just joined the Night Raid!
Wait,
don't I get a say in this?!
Just give up.
Leone always gets her way.
Look at that, my best friend
knows how it works!
Bulat, he's all yours.
Put me down!
I don't wanna murder people!
[BULAT] Aww! It gets easier.
Huh? What does?
The mission is now complete.
We're heading back.
[TATSUMI]
Huh?! Where are we going?!
Awww, how did I get
myself into this?!
[music playing]