Is this some sort of dream?
[TATSUMI]
Nope... unfortunately
this is not a dream.
[Reel winding]
[LUBBOCK]
Huh? Looks like someone's
coming up from the valley.
He's pretty fast too!
Who is this guy?!
[SYURA]
They practically wiped out
all of Stylish's creations!
[LUBBOCK]
I should probably hide for now.
Tatsumi's not back yet.
I'm starting to get
a really bad feeling.
[SYURA]
Hello, Imperial Capital?
So good to be back! Hehe...
ESDEATH
Hehe... I'd know your
scent anywhere;
good to see you Tatsumi!
So tell me why you ran away.
I've missed you so much.
Wha?! What're you doing here?!
Silly boy.
I'm here to capture
the Danger Beasts
attacking the Capital.
Uh... Which leads me to the
question of why you're here.
Uh!
She's onto me!
I'm dead if I can't come up
with something good.
Oh yeah about that, um,
before I tell you do you think
maybe you could let go of me?
I will not.
Um, please it
makes me nervous
when we're close
together like this.
I'm not letting you go.
Uh... I'm testing myself!
I heard that there were some
Danger Beasts on the mountain!
A man after my own heart.
Well? Did you join the
Revolutionary Army yet?
Uh...
No, not yet.
But I'm still planning to
enlist as soon as I can.
I guess you could say
that's the reason
I'm out here trying to
hone my skills.
Yes. I see that.
Judging by the amount of
muscle you've built up
I'd wager your abilities
have exponentially grown.
You've obviously been
working hard!
And with so much
room to improve!
You really think so?
I do not have time
for any of this!
[ESDEATH]
The Danger Beasts are
almost all gone.
They have really been
a nuisance...
But honestly, thanks to them
we're together again!
Love is a strange thing!
Uh, eh...
How can there be so
many interruptions
on a deserted mountain?
You there!
The coward trying to hide.
Show yourself.
If you refuse, you'll get
no mercy from me!
[SYURA]
Well shit, I thought you
wouldn't notice me.
Not too shabby.
Now I understand why everyone
is so bloody terrified of you.
Anyway, now that the two of us
have finally exchanged
pleasantries...
it's probably a good time
for me to stop playing
with my little toys.
Sounds like you know something
about why Danger Beasts are
roaming this area.
I'd be more than glad
to torture it out of you.
Sorry madam, but that's
not my cup of tea.
But if you're in need of
a little excitement
I'm willing to let you play
with my toys as well!
Behold my Imperial Arms!
Shambala!
What's happening?!
Now then...
I wonder what kind of game
we should play next.
Uhhh...
WHERE ARE WE?!
Uh.. Miss Esdeath...
could you hit me
really hard?
Tatsumi... I didn't know
you were into that.
We really are perfect for each
other, isn't it wonderful?
Oh god, that's not what I meant!
I just want to find out
if that guy trapped us
in some kind of illusion,
that's all!
So if you were to hurt me, maybe
I'd snap out of it, you know?!
Understood.
As you wish.
Uh!
Mmm...
It's not an illusion.
Our surroundings feel too real.
The cool breeze
blowing on the waves...
The warm sunshine...
Everything around us is true.
Then what happened?
I assume this was somehow
caused by that man we saw.
How did he manage
to teleport us?
That can't be possible, right?!
[ESDEATH]
The Empire has 48 legendary
weapons known as Imperial Arms.
Rumor has it that the
secret art of a lost nation
was used to create one that
could manipulate space itself.
Uh! That's crazy!
Wait, hang on.
Isn't that basically
what Incursio does
every time I summon its armor?
Oh man...
when I think about it like that
it kinda freaks me out!
[ESDEATH]
Of all the Imperial Arms,
I can only think of a
handful with the power
to control space.
Who was that man?
Let's take a look around.
[Tatsumi screams]
Ah!
Oh crap, there's
nothing but ocean!
But isn't this a
gorgeous view?
It's starting to feel
kind of like we're on a date,
isn't it, my darling?
I'd rather start
with dinner first.
You never know what can happen
when dealing with Imperial Arms.
In my line of work you have to
be able to adapt immediately.
I'm sure you do.
[ESDEATH]
Now, where were we?
Uh...
Right, we're on a date!
Wanna cuddle?
Hey, stop it!
[Rumbling]
[ESDEATH]
Well he's a big fella.
[TATSUMI]
It looks just like Dr. Stylish
after he used that trump card!
Even with everyone in
Night Raid working together,
it was still a close fight!
Do the two of us
even stand a chance?
He's after us!
I won't let him ruin
our time together.
You are interrupting!
You deserve to be impaled!
Weiss Schnabel!
[TATSUMI]
She's even stronger
than I thought.
You're still standing.
This is getting interesting.
[TATSUMI]
Hey... you see that weird spot
on his forehead?
Doesn't it look kinda weak?
I was thinking the same thing.
We must be soulmates!
Grau Horn!
He's quite stubborn.
[TATSUMI]
Ahhhhh!
[ESDEATH]
Tatsumi?!
Ah!
Well done!
Though I had originally
planned on winning your heart
with my own skills...
you wound up deepening
my love for you.
And here I used some of my
favorite moves and everything!
[Crashing]
There's another one!
Leave it to me, Tatsumi,
I'll give him what he deserves!
Hagel Sprung!
Heh!
Wow, I cannot believe
the size of that attack.
She's on a whole
different level.
So this is how
General Esdeath fights.
Akame... how the heck
are you going to kill her?!
[TATSUMI]
Those two must have been
the last of them.
[ESDEATH]
So that was what he meant by
"picking up his toys."
Which means this was where
he was hiding that new breed
of Danger Beast.
So what do you want to do
after our break?
First we'll
explore the area
so we can develop a
better understanding
of our situation.
Good idea.
We still don't know what
we're dealing with.
We'll only make things
worse if we panic.
It's best to
remain calm.
Alright! Let's get to work!
Wait, did I really
just say that?
She's the enemy, remember?!
[ESDEATH]
Mmm... not quite right.
[Tropical music playing]
We searched the island for
so long the sun went down huh.
Yes... and it's been
a lovely time.
Uh... oh, yeah.
[ESDEATH]
Not only that,
but I also managed to
figure out where we are.
Oh!
This island is
several miles
to the southeast
of the Empire.
What? You've gotta be
kidding me.
Wow, I had no idea
we were so far away.
Which means...
You and I are the only
two people on this
island, Tatsumi.
So, then... what would
you like to do?
You're in charge.
Go ahead, choose your fate.
Well, don't all those options
mean about the same thing?!
Aw, you're no fun at all.
[TATSUMI]
How can you be so calm and
easy‐going about this?
Of course I'm calm;
I'm the one who knows
how to get back.
‐Don't worry.
‐Huh?!
However, I'll need
you to give me your
full cooperation.
Is that clear?
Uh, yeah!
I've got a really bad
feeling about this.
But if things get chaotic
I might have a chance to
make a break for it.
All I can do is hope!
[ESDEATH]
Just as I thought,
the secret was in
WHERE he transported us.
[TATSUMI]
So, does that mean
he can only teleport
to places that
have this mark?
[ESDEATH]
Based on the size of the light
when it activated,
I'd say it only works on
a few people at a time.
And it must use a large
amount of energy,
so he can't do it very often.
So you think..
if we stay by this spot...
[ESDEATH]
The gate should open
again eventually.
But this is only the
first way I found.
Now. Before I tell you
the second way back,
there's something
I'd like to do.
Sure, what is it?
Now that we're
all by ourselves,
let's learn more
about each other.
[gasp] Ugh...
Whoa whoa whoa, time out!
If that's all you want
then there's a lot of
other ways to do it!
Want me to stop?
Okay. Then you have to
answer my questions.
First off: where did
you learn to fight
with a sword?
Uh, well, there was
this veteran who used to
live in my village.
Apparently he was a pretty good
martial arts teacher.
Anyway, I trained under him.
[ESDEATH]
Interesting.
Did he teach you about
blacksmithing as well?
[TATSUMI]
I tried to master as many
skills as I could
so I'd make a lot of money.
To accomplish something
like that takes a
lot of diligence.
You're very talented!
I, uh, get the
feeling that YOU
could accomplish
just about anything.
Not true. For example, I'll
never have an appreciation
of say, the arts.
The first time I heard
Nyau play the flute,
I couldn't understand
what was so special.
[TATSUMI]
This could be my chance
to get some information
out of her.
I mean, she's crazy about me,
how hard can it be?
Maybe I can find something
in our conversation
that'll help me convince
her to join our side.
To fight for us.
Let's face it...
I'd MUCH rather have her
as a friend than a foe!
So uh, Miss Esdeath..
you didn't grow up in
the Capital, did you?
That's right.
I was born close to
the Northern border.
I don't suppose you've
heard of the Partas clan?
I haven't.
[ESDEATH]
They were a hunting clan
that specialized in
killing Danger Beasts.
And I was the daughter
of their chief.
Since you were kind enough
to tell me about your past..
I guess I'll share mine.
[Roar]
[ESDEATH]
Father!
I caught my prey!
[FATHER]
Ah! Well done!
You're a good little hunter
for your age...
but I think your old‐man's
got you beat!
Wow!
We're about to begin the
butchering process.
‐Are ya ready?
‐Mm‐hm...
I went ahead and
weakened it.
And it's tied down
so it can't hurt us.
But let's be quick
just in case, okay?
[Roar]
It hurts my ears when
they scream like that.
Yeah, I can't do
much for the pain,
but the eggs are more valuable
if the beast is still alive.
Y'see, it used to survive
by devouring our people.
Not anymore, this time
the predator loses.
The hunter may have
been strong,
but in this case the hunted
ended up being
just a little bit
stronger in the end.
It's what it deserves for
being weaker than me.
Esdeath. Carve out the eyes
and the crest.
Mm‐hm...
I'll do my best, Father!
She never hesitates
to kill a target,
even if it's weak or
trying to run away.
She's a natural hunter.
But that being said...
I can't help but wonder
if she's missing something.
I can only hope it
won't be a problem.
[ESDEATH]
Eat or be eaten.
That's the kind of wonderful
lifestyle in which I was raised.
It was just us and
the Danger Beasts.
The way both sides desperately
fought for their lives
was so much fun.
‐Oh, an insect war?
‐Yeah.
It seems to me like the
fighting's already over.
Look over there, the enemy
soldiers have dragged the
queen out of the fortress
and they're getting
ready to lynch her.
That's what happens
to the weak, right?
Yes, Esdeath.
This situation is
exactly the same
as it was when your mother
was eaten by the Danger Beast.
Make no mistake, this is
how the world works.
It may be sad, but your mother
died because she was weak.
[ESDEATH]
The strong survive;
the weak become prey.
Camping in the mountains
these past few days paid off!
I caught this guy
all by myself!
Father is gonna be
so proud of me!
[Gasp]
What happened...?
[Groaning]
[ESDEATH]
What's going on?!
[VILLAGER]
The northern tribe just came
from across the border
and started attacking
our people.
The chief took charge and
killed a few dozen
of the bastards,
but then they ganged
up on him all at once and
he couldn't hold 'em off.
[Gasp]
[ESDEATH]
Father!
Esdeath...
it's like I've told you...
We were defeated because
we weren't strong enough.
This was our fate.
Never let yourself be of
the weak, Esdeath.
Never become the prey.
[ESDEATH]
I continued to hunt
Danger Beasts on my own,
but eventually
I ran out of prey,
so I became an
Imperial officer.
So somewhere
along the line
I switched from
preying on monsters
to targeting humans.
And well,
that's my story.
I get it.
You wanted revenge on
the northern tribe.
I can understand why
you hated them so much.
Hmm? I suppose that's what
it must look like...
but I don't
necessarily hate them.
What?
Well then what about
all those rumors of you
burying hundreds of
northerners alive?
I wanted to be
efficient when I made
an example of them.
Besides, I would
have done that
regardless of what
my feelings were.
I couldn't disobey
orders, you know.
Huh?
What happened to my father
was regrettable,
but it doesn't change the fact
that he was a weak man.
Is there anything else
you wanted to ask me?
I'm more than willing to
tell you whatever you
want to know, Tatsumi.
Uhh... actually...
I was kinda wondering if
maybe I could see what your
Imperial Arms looks like.
Oh, that?
My Imperial Arms...
Ahh...
[ESDEATH]
Look.
It's right here.
[TATSUMI]
What?!
It happened several years ago.
[MINISTER]
Hmm... I've offered
a variety of weapons,
but your affinity seems
poor with all of them.
Well, I am impressed with
how enormous this axe is...
but nothing's caught my eye.
Huh?
Is that an Imperial Arms
in that urn over there?
[MINISTER]
Yes, the Demon's Extract.
The blood of an S‐Class
Danger‐Beast from the far north.
A blood‐type weapon?
[MINISTER]
The legends say if you
drink the extract and
it resonates properly,
you'll be able to obtain
the Danger Beast's ability
to manipulate ice.
However, every warrior
to attempt to do so
has lost his mind
in the process.
That all sounds rather
fascinating, doesn't it?
You're not going to drink that!
You may have a
dangerous reputation,
but that doesn't mean
it'll bond with you!
[ESDEATH]
I feel so drawn to it...
as if it's beckoning me
to drink.
That's a good sign.
Perhaps the Extract
is right for you.
Maybe.
For some reason I feel certain
I was meant for this.
I honed my intuition
out in the wild;
if I'm wrong,
I deserve to die.
[MINISTER]
It should only take a sip
to know for sure.
No reason not to drink
the whole thing.
I bet that'll make me
even stronger.
I guess it can't drive you
insane if you already are.
Ahh...
My, that tasted so...
Gah!
Huh?!
[Random voices]
Kill! Steal! Murder!
Destroy! Humiliate!
Break! Slaughter!
[ESDEATH]
Hehe... HAHA...
The urge to destroy
is overwhelming!
Now I understand why
everyone else went crazy...
but I will NOT!
This is nothing!
I won't be bested by
a mere goblet of blood!
I will always be on top.
I will always be victorious...
no matter what gets in my way!
And I will answer to
no one but myself!
I'm feeling truly
delightful now, Minister.
The power's surging
through my entire body.
[MINISTER]
You seem to have
already merged.
To the birth of the world's
most powerful warrior...
Esdeath!
[TATSUMI]
So after all this time
that monster's blood
is still in your body?
[ESDEATH]
That's correct.
But I mastered it long ago,
you don't need to worry.
[TATSUMI]
So that's what made you
like to torture people?
Oh, no..
I've always enjoyed that.
[TATSUMI]
She didn't do it for revenge,
and it's not because that
Demon's Extract thing
makes her go berserk.
Either of those would've
been better than this.
She's been true to herself
from the very beginning...
nothing could change someone
with a personality like that!
I can't believe I was gonna
try to win her over again!
I'm such an idiot!
[SYURA]
Hmm.
I wonder how those
two are doing.
I'm sure they haven't gotten
themselves killed yet.
Perhaps it's about time
I re‐opened the portal, yes?
Shambala Point B, release.
That oughta do it.
[WOMAN]
Hmm... What are you
doing over there?
Huh? Excuse me, bitch?
You know, despite
your language,
you seem oddly...
refined.
Ha, well, no shit.
I mean, Minister Honest
is my father, so...
Huh, that man is your father?
Grrr...
Guh...
What the hell does a whore
have to say about it, huh?!
[Woman crying]
I happen to have great
respect for him...
but I can do far
better than he has.
I consider surpassing
your parents
to be a good show of
filial piety, don't you?!
[TATSUMI]
So uh...
about that second way
back you found...
[ESDEATH]
Oh yes, I'm sure
I can tell you now.
We just need to secure a ride.
There are quite a few
species of Danger Beasts
that will let you
ride on their backs.
Although.. sometimes it's a
little difficult to train them
not to throw you off.
You'd better let me do it.
[TATSUMI]
Wait, isn't that one up there?
[ESDEATH]
Huh? I guess it is.
That's too bad.
Be right back.
Wait, what? How are you
planning on catching it?
It's way too far up in the sky!
[ESDEATH]
I'll train it after I
shoot it down!
Just watch!
[Sigh]
Ah!
Whoa, it opened!
This is my perfect chance
to get outta here!
Hmm...
But, she did look after me
this whole time.
I should return the favor.
Look, Miss Esdeath!
The portal's opening up again!
I'm going through, okay?!
Ah! Tatsumi, wait!
Don't go in there!
[ESDEATH]
This is the same mountain
we were on yesterday.
Tatsumi, are you here?
Did he really get that far ahead
of me in those few seconds?
Impossible, he didn't
have that much time.
[TATSUMI]
Even though I'm invisible,
she'll feel my aura if I move.
All I can do now,
is wait 'til she leaves.
[ESDEATH]
He's not here.
Could it be... he was
sent to another location?
I lost him again.
But one thing is certain...
now that we've found
each other a second time,
I'm sure it won't be the last.
Fate will bring you back
to me... I can feel it.
[TATSUMI]
I can feel it too.
But now, I know for sure I'll
never persuade you to join us.
So the next time
the two of us meet...
it will be as enemies.
[Music playing]