[TATSUMI]
So this is the Capital's
red‐light district.
I'm a little nervous.
[LEONE]
Aww. Tatsumi, you're so cute
when you act all bashful!
Anyway. That money ain't gonna
make itself, so I say
we get cooking!
Lionel, transform!
Ha! When I get into beast mode
I feel like I can just
take on the whole world!
[Tatsumi clapping]
[LEONE]
C'mon, let's get in there
and make a mess of things.
Wha?
[TATSUMI]
Wait, hold on! Ahhh!
Not so fast!
Whew. It looks like we made it!
[TATSUMI]
But I thought we were
gonna "sneak in"...
[Chatter and giggling]
Look at this.
Huh?
[Giggling]
Uh...
[Door opens]
[BOSS]
Ooh, they sure are
goin' to town!
If you want me to
bring you more,
better keep bein' good
little girls, you understand?
Okay!
Huh?
[Girl giggles]
[LACKEY]
Hey Boss, what about
that one over there?
[BOSS]
Eh, I'm done with her.
Her mind's gone and
she stinks of fish.
Just get rid of her.
These bitches are
pretty easy to replace.
[GIRL]
Please... I need more!
[LACKEY]
Hm? Here.
[Punching]
[GIRL] Ow!
[LEONE][grunts]
[LACKEY]
I guess we need to go and pick
up a few more from the slums.
[BOSS]
Yeah, these bitches
are a dime a dozen.
Show 'em a little money, and
they'll do whatever you want.
This is even more sick than
the client said it was.
Those bastards!
That girl he was just hitting...
she was a friend of mine
from back home.
Now I'm pissed!
Let's just slaughter these pukes
and be done with it!
Roger that!
[LACKEY]
It looks like we're in
prime position
to move and expand the drug
route a little bit, huh?
[BOSS]
Yeah, probably so.
I'll have a talk
with Mr. Chiburu
and see how he feels about it.
[BAD GUYS]
Huh?
[BOTH]
We're here to send every
single one of you...
straight to Hell!
Get those punks!
Bring back their heads!
[Guys charging]
[Grunt]
Every person in this
trafficking ring is our target.
Which means all of you
are about to die.
Get ready for some pain, fellas!
Uh... Kill her!
[Grunting]
Ahh!
Ah!
Ugh...
[Trembling]
I'm‐I'm not gonna die...
I'm not gonna let you kill me!
[Gasp]
Then you'll have to move
faster than that, right?
[Gasps]
[Choking]
Please, take whatever you want.
You want money?
You want drugs?
I'll give you anything.
I'll give you everything.
Just let me go, please!
Anything I want, huh?
Thanks, but the only thing
I want from you is your life.
Who the hell are
you people anyway?!
[Choking]
Hehe...
Oh, we're just "bitches"!
[Groan]
I mean, honestly...
who better than a couple of
"bitches" to take you out?
[TATSUMI]
Uh, could you come up with
something else to
call us, please?
[TATSUMI]
So, what's gonna happen
to all those girls?
They're really messed up now.
[LEONE]
Unfortunately, that's not
really our call.
I know, but still.
[LEONE]
There's a retired doctor
who still lives around here.
I'll let him know what happened.
He'd probably be more than
happy to lend a hand.
The doc always was fond of
pretty girls, so everybody wins.
Know what I'm sayin?
That's great.
Heh. See, I knew you had
a little soft side.
I used to be friends with one of
those women, that's all it is.
That's the only reason
I wanted to help.
[TATSUMI]
Well, I don't care why.
Uh?
All that matters is
that those girls
get another chance
to start over.
[LEONE]
‐Tatsumi.
‐Hm?
[LEONE]
I've been meaning to
tell you something...
When you let yourself smile...
you're really sweet.
Ah!
Wh‐wh‐wha?!
[Leone laughs]
You can't run away now;
I've already marked
my territory!
Once you finally grow up,
you're gonna be all mine, baby.
Well anyway,
I wonder how the other group's
doing right about now?
That Chiburu guy was so
obnoxiously careful
I thought we'd never
track him down!
Yeah that's true,
but at least we completed
the mission on time!
[Leaves rustling]
Uh?
[Gasp]
Tehe...
Who is that?
Is it an enemy?
I couldn't sense her at all!
The other guards can't
conceal their auras,
so she must be on a
completely different level!
[SERYU]
I know you...
you're the one from
the wanted posters.
Sheele of Night Raid, I presume?
And judging by your
friend's weapon
I'd guess that she's from
Night Raid too.
I'm so glad I spent
the night on watch
or I never would have
found the two of you.
Finally...
Oh, how badly I've been
wanting to meet you, Night Raid!
I'm Imperial Guard member
Seryu Ubiquitous!
And in the name of
absolute justice...
I'll banish your evil
right here and now!
[Clock ticking]
Well now that you've
blown my cover,
you can either die
where you're standing
or you can come with us.
[SERYU]
They say you're wanted
dead or alive.
So that means
I can execute you!
Bandits like you are the
reason my Father was killed
in the line of duty!
And you were the ones
who murdered my mentor,
Captain Ogre!
I'll never forgive you,
Night Raid!
So you're that eager to
fight us, huh?
Fine. I'll make it quick!
[Little growl]
[Gunfire]
Did I get her yet?
[Huge growl]
Y'see that....
is that what I think it is?
I'm afraid so.
This girl has an organic
type of Imperial Arms.
Tonfa guns!
[SERYU]
Looks like shooting won't be
effective from this distance.
Koro! Suppertime!
[Roars]
[SHEELE]
I'm sorry.
Heh...
[Roar]
[Gasps]
[Roars]
[Roars in pain]
Don't you even remember what
the book said, Sheele?!
Organic type Imperial Arms
always have a hidden core
you have to destroy;
otherwise they just
keep regenerating!
And it doesn't have a heart
so Akame's sword won't
do any good either.
This is a surprisingly
nasty opponent!
Koro. Bulk up.
[Growls]
Bleh. That's not cute.
Crush her!
[Roars]
[SHEELE]
Mine! Just stay behind me.
[Roars]
Ugh! Ah!
[Whistle blows]
Huh?
[Giggles]
[Sheele straining]
[MINE]
This thing is too strong
to defeat...
and she just called in
reinforcements.
That means we're in big
trouble... perfect!
[Growls]
You still hungry, little guy.
Eat this!
[Roars]
Uh! Did her weapon just improve?
[Groan]
Damn! It's already starting
to regenerate again.
This is not good.
[Seryu laughs]
You should never underestimate
an Imperial Arms!
Huh?
One thing about weapons,
they can't keep moving
if the wielder is dead.
[SERYU]
They were after me all along!
[SHEELE]
Better use my trump card!
Extase!
[SERYU]
How is that thing giving off
so much light?!
You've run out of time.
[Gasps]
[Screams]
Ugh!
[SHEELE]
She's even strong
without her weapon!
[Growls]
[MINE]
Hey you.
You're supposed to be
fighting me.
Stop getting sidetracked.
Pumpkin's not as powerful now
that the threat's cooled off.
But I can still keep him busy!
Now that I've hit him
a few times,
I'm starting to narrow down
where the core is.
Ugh!
Ah!
Uh!
Ahh!
[SHEELE]
She sacrificed her arms to
block that fatal strike!
True justice...
ALWAYS WINS!
[SHEELE]
That's part of her body?!
It was a special gift
from Captain Ogre!
Just for you!
[Gunshot]
[SERYU]
She blocked it!
Ahh!
Ugh...
[SERYU]
I'm not done yet!
If I do this,
Koro will overheat
and he won't be able
to move for a while.
Heh. Screw it.
Koro, use your trump card!
Go berserk!
[Growling]
[Roar]
[Grunting]
[MINE]
It's got a trump card?!
Sheele!
Hold on!
Good boy... now SQUEEZE!
Ugh!
Ah!
Uh...
You did it!
That was a close one!
[Gunshot]
[SHEELE]
What's happening?
I can't move...
[SERYU]
Justice prevails!
[Growls]
[Gasp]
[Roars]
[Sobbing]
No...
Sheele!
Goddamn you...
You just killed Sheele,
you bitch.
[Straining]
Ah! Dammit, my arm.
Aaah!
[Gasp]
[Footsteps]
[Breathes in]
What?!
What the hell, I can't see!
[GUARD]
Aagh! Careful, men!
We don't know what it is!
[Gasp]
[Soft music plays]
Extase...
Sheele, no!
That demon!
How can she possibly
keep on fighting?!
Get out of here, Mine...
while you still have a chance!
Hurry!
No, I... I can't!
[Crying]
[SHEELE]
Oh, Mine...
I'm glad... I could be
useful in the end.
[Grunt]
Koro!
Finish her!
[Sighs]
[SHEELE]
Night Raid...
You were always home to me.
I loved every one of you...
from the bottom of my heart.
I had so much fun.
[sigh]
Tatsumi... I'm sorry.
I won't be able to
hold you ever again.
[Bite]
[Clank]
[Raindrops]
[Guard]
What? What happened to
the light? Where'd it go?
You gonna be okay?
We really need to get back.
[Koro munching]
[Seryu giggling]
[SERYU]
I did it!
It would've been even better
if she'd abandoned her friend
like the traitor she is.
I guess she was just too stupid!
[Guard shocked]
Daddy? Are you proud, now that I
took down one of the bad people?
Do you see how brightly the
light of justice was shining?!
[Laughing]
[TATSUMI]
Who did this?
Tell me who did it, now!
Mine!
Mine! Tell me, dammit!
Calm down, Tatsumi.
Why do you need to
know that now?
So we can get our revenge!
Don't you get it?!
Not yet.
Act too quickly and you'll
only add to the body count.
Then how do you expect me
to act?! Huh?!
I'm not just gonna
sit on my ass and‐
Ugh...
That's enough, Tatsumi!
Now pull yourself together!
We warned you that any one of us
can die at any time.
You accepted that risk the
moment you decided to join us.
[Grunts]
[Akame softly cries]
[MINE]
It was your mission.
You wanted payback for
what we did to you...
I know that.
But you took Sheele
away from us.
And I'm sure you'll be coming
for the rest of us too.
But when that time comes...
I swear on my life,
Seryu Ubiquitous...
I will have your head!
[NAJENDA]
Our associate's death was
by no means in vain.
The Empire's seen
what weapons we have.
They'll be attacking with more
and more Imperial Arms.
This means that our chances
to obtain Imperial Arms
will vastly increase.
Remember, Tatsumi.
These battles are always
to the death.
[Wind blows]
[Gasps]
I'm finally back. I'm home.
[Music playing]