[MINE] I'm going.
And I won't let you stop me.
[AKAME] It's a trap.
[MINE] I don't need you
to tell me that.
But still...
I won't just sit here
and watch them execute Tatsumi!
You've really changed, Mine.
Remember when you were
trying to stop me?
Please don't say something
stupid like we need to save him.
That won't work.
That was a long time ago.
Tatsumi means something
different to me now.
[AKAME] I'm going too.
[MINE] (huh?)
There's no reason to put
yourself in danger.
That's stupid!
What you're planning is stupid!
If we do this together,
we have a greater chance
of making it back.
Y'know, you're starting to sound
just like him with all that
pathetic optimism.
You're just as bad as me,
if not worse.
[MINE] (urk!) (hmpf!)
Fine, you can tag along
if it means that much to you!
[LEONE] Sounds like a plan!
[MINE] Leone!
[LEONE] I'm the one who
saw Tatsumi's potential
and pushed for him to join us
in the first place.
If he were to get himself
executed at this point
in the game,
it would make me
look like a jerk.
So...
Does that mean you're on board?
[LEONE]
We've made up our minds, Boss.
Hope you're okay with it.
[NAJENDA] Why would I have
a problem with that?
[MINE] The boss?
[NAJENDA] If they're holding a
public execution
with the intention of weakening
the Revolutionary Army's morale,
then it's our responsibility
to put a stop to it.
Besides, I have no doubt we're
going to need Tatsumi and
Incursio in the final battle.
Awww!
It's okay, we know you miss him.
[NAJENDA] (hmm?)
(short chuckle)
Oh, you know I'm right.
Then consider this
an emergency mission.
Let's go get Tatsumi.
[ESDEATH] Tatsumi...
[ESDEATH]
It's been a while, Tatsumi.
I can't believe YOU
were part of Night Raid.
I came in here
ready to destroy you,
but all my anger was gone
once I saw your face.
You must be so unhappy.
It's not too late to join me.
If you do, I promise I'll
forgive all your transgressions.
Never!
I will not fight for the Empire.
[schlang]
If you won't accept my offer,
then you know what
must happen.
I will die for what I believe.
[ESDEATH] I won't ask
where your friends are.
All I want is for you
to stand beside me.
[TATSUMI]
Why are you so fixated on me?
[ESDEATH]
My heart was drawn to you.
I want us to be together,
Tatsumi.
[TATSUMI] No!
[ESDEATH] (gasps)
I could never be with someone
who's only desires in this world
are creating war
and destruction!
Is that right?
Then have it your way.
I will perform your execution
with my own hands.
That way I can see for myself
the strength of your resolve.
[WAVE] The commander said she
was in love with Tatsumi, right?
So why is she doing this?
[RUN]
Well, I suppose you could think
of it as an act of passion.
(huh?)
Our orders were very clear.
Tomorrow during the execution,
palace defenses will be
thinner than usual.
We'll be expected
to provide backup.
[WAVE] But what is she thinking,
killing the one she loves?
It just doesn't
make sense to me.
[KUROME]
I understand how she feels.
Instead of letting
somebody else kill him,
she wants to be
the one to do it.
Just like how I want
to kill my sister.
It's because I love her.
But now... it's...
It's too late.
I'm out of time.
I can't...
[NAJENDA]
My sources have informed me that
the Great General Budo will be
attending the public execution
along with Esdeath.
Who's Budo?
He's the only great general
in the empire
and he has the loyalty
of all the guards.
And his weapon, Adramelech,
is quite terrifying.
Wow!
[NAJENDA] Susanoo?
Are you ready to use
your trump card?
Yes,
once you've given me the word,
I can activate it as needed.
[NAJENDA]
We must complete this mission
and prove our comrades
didn't die in vain.
Thank you for
your loyal service.
Thank you, Lubbock.
[crowd cheering]
People of this great nation!
We are most distraught
by the rebels
spreading unfounded rumors
about the fall of Our empire.
Disregard these allegations.
We would like to assure you that
the empire is alive and well!
Today, one of their members
shall be put to death,
in atonement for this
traitorous behavior!
The Revolutionary Army has
caused great unrest,
with these murderous criminals
as their spearhead!
And by brandishing
the blade of greed,
they've deceived honest people.
They're nothing but
a violent gang of assassins!
[crowd cheering]
No matter what your numbers,
and no matter what
falsehoods you perpetuate,
We will not allow you
to poison Our city!
Mark my words: Our great
empire will never fall!
[crowd cheering]
We've done well,
haven't We, Minister?
Impeccable as always,
Your Majesty.
General Esdeath, you may lop off
his head whenever you're ready.
Hold on.
Where do you think you're going?
Excuse us, it's time for lunch.
Come along, Your Grace.
[EMPEROR] (hmm?) Lunch already?
Then, could you oversee the
execution, Budo? Please?
[BUDO] Of course.
[MINSTER]
Oh, I'm quite famished!
[BUDO] So the minister's
making his escape.
[crowd cheering increases]
[BUDO] (hmm?)
[ESDEATH]
I know precisely where to cut
whether I want to maim
or I want to kill.
[shwack]
You told me you were prepared
to die, did you not?
If you're the man
I think you are,
then you'll show me
how strong your spirit is!
(huh?!)
Way to go, dummy!
You weren't supposed
to get caught, y'know!
Oh, no. What're you doing?!
[MINE] You are not allowed to
worry me like that ever again!
[gunshots]
[TATSUMI] (screams)
Hey, watch where you're
aiming that thing!
Well, look who's here.
[panic & commotion]
So you finally came out to play.
Well, you didn't leave me
much of an option.
(laughs)
Spoken like a true coward.
It's been a long time.
Whaddya say we do
some catching up?
In my torture chamber.
Thanks, but I'm not really
into that stuff.
I think I'll pass.
[explosions]
I'm glad you set up those
charges before you left,
Lubbock.
We didn't plan this, but
they're being put to good use!
[explosions]
I'd never suspect you'd enter
the fray without a strategy.
It's so much fun.
You must be here to rescue your
little partner, eh, Night Raid?!
[NAJENDA] Let's go!
[LEONE] Right!
[SUSANOO] Understood.
You handle General Budo
for me, okay?
What? But how am I supposed to
fight a guy with hair like that?
[BUDO]
Revolutionary filth like you
should never be permitted
to set foot inside
the sacred coliseum!
Prepare to be destroyed by
my Imperial Arms!
(hyah!)
[AKAME]
Since you won't surrender...
[SOLDIERS] (yaaahhh!)
You must die.
[ESDEATH]
Is that your Imperial Arms?
[NAJENDA] It is.
I am Susanoo.
[ESDEATH]
I don't care what it's called.
It won't need a name...
after this!
Back off!
(hyaaahhh!)
(laughing)
Very nice! Keep it up!
(screams)
Man, you'd be easier to save
if you weren't so damn tiny!
Do you really think this is the
time to start picking on me?
Look out!
[explosion]
Ow, that hurt!
You must be their
close‐range fighter!
Take the shot, hurry!
If she does,
it'll surely kill you too!
Oh no, my healing ability
is pretty badass.
Guess I have to trust you!
[power‐up whine]
[gunshot]
[explosion]
(gasps)
[LEONE] (ungh)
I didn't expect it to
paralyze my whole body!
[BUDO] An impressive
team you have here.
First that young man on the
crucifix, and now you two.
It's regrettable that
you've chosen the path of
wickedness and treason.
Who cares what you think?!
Whether it's the right one or
not, the path will be my own,
thank you very much!
Mine!
[MINE] (screams)
Oh really now?
You finished already?
Clearly, you don't realize
what my weapon can do.
This is my
Adventurous Bunker Pumpkin.
And its firepower gets deadlier
the more dangerous the
situation!
It's to my advantage to have my
back up against the wall!
The greater the threat,
the stronger I get!
[gunshot]
It's not charged enough yet!
[SOLDIER]
You're not getting through!
[sounds of battle & screams]
Found it!
Hang in there, Tatsumi.
[SUSANOO] (gasps)
[ESDEATH] Now freeze.
(chuckles)
Susanoo!
[ESDEATH] What a shame.
[ESDEATH] And to think I used
to have so much respect
for you as a general.
I hope you have more to offer.
[NAJENDA]
Why was I saving my energy?
This is Esdeath
I'm dealing with!
Magatama Manifest!
What are you up to?
Night Raid must be more
resilient than you think
if we've survived this long.
Even if he IS frozen solid,
I wouldn't let my guard
down just yet.
Are you ready now, Susanoo?
It's time to defeat Esdeath!
Must be your trump card.
This should be good.
(hyaahh!)
But it won't be enough
to overpower me.
You must realize that
you're outmatched!
Eight‐Handed Mirror Shield!
She always has something.
[explosions]
Man, this guy's annoying!
Look out, he's gaining on you!
Don't worry, Tatsumi!
I know it looks pretty serious
from where you are,
but I'm getting ready to
turn the tables on this loser
and save you!
[BUDO] Well then, it appears
you possess everything it takes
to master that Imperial Arms.
It seems to be fluently
resonating with your
every emotion!
Eat this!
[gunshot]
[BUDO] Either way,
you're not going to win!
You're about to eat those words,
you pile of crap!
[MINE] (screams)
Mine, no!
[MINE] I'm okay, Tatsumi.
Don't you remember?
I made a promise to myself,
I was gonna make something of
my life, didn't I?
My strength...
is Pumpkin's strength!
(ngngh) (coughs)
I'm not finished yet!
[BUDO]
Out of mercy, I'll go ahead and
put you out of your misery.
I don't need mercy from you.
All of my people are going to
walk out of this place alive.
I'm not losing any more friends!
I'm not!
Allow me to demonstrate
the ultimate power of
Adramelech's trump card!
Solid Shooter!
This is bad!
Mine, don't!
[powering‐up whine]
Please, Pumpkin... Please.
Channel my feelings!
[BUDO] Say goodbye, little girl!
Tatsumi!
[MINE] (grunts in exertion)
YOU CAN'T KILL ME!
[gunshot]
What? No! (screams)
(loud thud)
I... won...
Hold on!
[shwick]
Tatsumi!
Mine!
[TATSUMI] (ungh!)
[TATSUMI] Please... not this!
Oh no...
(grrr!)
The mission's complete!
Get back to base, NOW!
Tatsumi, I won't let you leave!
Sacred Sword of the Heavens!
I gotcha!
[click]
[explosions]
Everything in sight
will be encased in ice.
Mahapadma!
That ability puts such
enormous strain on me,
I'm not capable of using it
as often as I'd like.
Too much would be
overkill, anyway.
What... what happened?
Esdeath, what did you do?!
Oh, I just froze time and space.
It's my special trump card
that I developed for
just such an occassion.
I wanted something that would
not only keep Tatsumi
from escaping,
but effectively slay my enemies.
SUSANOO, GET OUT OF THERE!
I suppose I should congratulate
you for inspiring me to use it.
Susanoo's core!
(shocked gasp)
[ESDEATH] You lose.
Now if you'll accompany me
to the torture chambers...
What?! Impossible!
It's regenerating itself!
This makes three times.
It's our last shot.
It'll take everything
I have left.
If I exhaust my life force,
I'm sure I can make him
even more powerful.
[coughs]
If General Budo is dead,
then my life was well spent.
I can die peacefully
knowing that.
The rest is up to you, Susanoo.
[ESDEATH] Burn in Hell, Najenda!
Celestial Treasure Magatama!
Well, he just boosted his power.
(kyaaahhh!)
[TATSUMI] Su, let me help you!
[NAJENDA] Run away, Tatsumi.
[TATSUMI]
But he's powered up now!
[NAJENDA] It's just the way
his attacks overlapped.
It's making it appear as though
Susanoo's strength increased
by double.
But the level he is right now,
he'll never even come close
to defeating Esdeath.
[TATSUMI] Su!
It looks like you've
gotten tougher,
but you're still
not strong enough.
Despite your best efforts,
you're still losing this fight.
[TATSUMI] Don't do it!
[SUSANOO]
Please try not to forget
the reason we came here
in the first place.
Run, Tatsumi.
[TATSUMI] But, Su...
In my thousand years as
an Imperial Arms,
my time with this group has been
the most fun I've ever had.
I have no regrets.
Susanoo...
I bid you farewell.
[ESDEATH] Stop right there!
[SUSANOO] I don't think so!
That mirror again.
I will never let you
catch up to them!
So you're using yourself
as a shield
in order to buy time
for your companions to escape.
Where does Najenda find all
these mushy little softies?
I am nothing more than a weapon.
And now I have no trump card.
Given my situation,
wouldn't you agree
that this is my best
possible option?
[ESDEATH] You said your name
was Susanoo, yes?
[SUSANOO] So you WERE listening.
I will forever remember it as
the name of a legendary warrior,
and NOT an Imperial Arms.
Now, as you face your demise,
I will enjoy watching your
sad attempts to avoid
your inevitable end.
[SUSANOO] (yaaahhh!)
[TATSUMI]
We're going back to the base.
Just hang in there!
You'll be all healed up
in no time.
Put me down.
[TATSUMI] Don't be an idiot.
Your injuries are serious.
[MINE] Just do it, okay?
[MINE] Tatsumi?
[TATSUMI] I'm right here.
Ever since you saved me
back in Kyoroku,
I've been trying to find
a way to repay you.
That's why I‐
[TATSUMI] No...
You didn't have to do that!
We can... call it even now.
Yeah, sure! We're even.
Just don't give up on me,
all right?!
[MINE] You're so stupid.
I can't just heal myself
like Leone does.
[TATSUMI] (sobs)
I wanted to be...
I wanted to be by
your side 'til the end.
[TATSUMI] Don't talk like that!
'Cause we're supposed to be...
together...
Together forever!
You're such a bad liar,
Tatsumi.
And you're...
the biggest crybaby I ever met.
[TATSUMI] I can't believe you...
Why did you have to save me?
If it meant you were gonna...
You can't just... (sobs)
A man... should never let
anyone see him cry.
Hey...
Tatsumi?
[TATSUMI] Yeah?
I'm glad I...
I'm glad I fell
in love with you.
Mine...
You can't die...
PLEASE don't die!
You have to survive and make
something of your life, right?!
What are you talking about?
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
I already... I already did.
I love... you.
[MINE] (sighs)
[TATSUMI] (gasps)
[TATSUMI] Mine...
Mine, no!
Mine! (sobs)