[OLDER OFFICER]
Another castle
surrendered without a fight!
Cowards. Don't these people
have any loyalty anymore?
The viceroys of these castles
were relocated to
the countryside
because their behavior showed
signs of insubordination
against His Majesty.
It comes as no surprise.
But Minister, if this continues,
the rebel army will reach
the Imperial‐
[BUDO]
There's no need to panic.
[OLDER OFFICER]
Great General Budo!
A general should refrain from
getting involved in politics.
I've lived by those words
for quite some time now.
However I'm finding it a
challenge to keep my mouth shut
when it comes to something
like this, Minister.
Hohoho...
I'm not sure what to say!
I will protect this Empire.
It is a responsibility handed
down through my family line
for the past thousand years.
As such, I will personally
annihilate anyone who dares
to disrupt the peace of
this great nation...
regardless of who
may interfere.
[MINISTER]
Admirable! But there's
no reason for concern.
Even if the citizens
rise in rebellion,
we have plans in place
to overpower them.
Gentlemen...
Allow me to introduce
an elite force
I've assembled to
protect the Capital.
[Door opens]
[SYURA]
Hello Hellooo.
[Gasps]
This is my son, Syura.
I've decided to appoint
him to serve as the
company's commander.
Hm? You must be the
"Great" General I've
heard so much about.
You're like tied with
Esdeath for scariest
in the Empire.
Anyway, you shouldn't waste time
worrying about some commoners
and their revolution bullshit.
Why not let me handle it?
Oh? Going out?
If there's one thing I've
learned from battle,
it's that you can always
find a few rats around
before the entire swarm
makes an appearance.
Seriously.
Can't he just sit in the
castle and look pretty.
[MINISTER]
Listen, Son.
This is your chance
to prove yourself.
Whether or not I choose you
to be my successor
will depend on your performance.
Very well.
Hope you enjoy the show.
But first, I have a few rats of
my own to hunt down. Hehe...
[WAVE]
It's so empty in here lately.
Kurome, do you feel better now?
Honestly?
[KUROME]
I'm... okay.
Hmm...
[RUN]
I did the best I could,
but I doubt it'll taste as good
as what Bols used to make.
Wave, have you heard about
the new security force?
Apparently they report
directly to the Minister.
[WAVE] Yeah?
[RUN]
Well, I suppose we probably
should've seen it coming.
The Commander's on
an expedition,
and half our team members
have been assassinated.
[WAVE]
But isn't that even more of a
reason to move the rest of the
Jaegers to the frontline?
Why would they
put us on standby?
[RUN]
It tells me that there must be
some disagreement in the
Capital's central command.
[WAVE]
What the hell are
they thinking?!
It's times like these
we have to pull together.
It's the only way to bring down
the Revolutionary Army.
More please!
Are you serious?
Jeez. How can you even
eat at a time like this?
Hehe...
Help yourself.
[Plate breaks]
Uh...
[WAVE]
She fainted!
Oh God!
Kurome!
What's wrong?!
Can you hear me?
Kurome!
Wake up!
Open your eyes!
Kurome!
[TATSUMI]
They're sending out
more soldiers.
[LUBBOCK]
Yeah. This place is starting
to look like a battlefield.
[TATSUMI]
So the plan is to wait out here
for the perfect moment
and sneak into the palace.
And then we can
kill the Minister.
Are you sure you're ready
to do this, Tatsumi?
It's what we have to do.
Remember, it's important
that we minimize
the number of innocent
people involved.
The best way to do that
is get rid of the Minister
as quickly as possible.
Well put.
[LUBBOCK]
Oh, it's almost time for our
meeting with the resistance.
Let's go.
[MINE]
It's hard to believe how complex
these waterways are.
[LEONE]
I think they got bigger as the
Imperial Capital got bigger...
pretty wild.
But their maintenance is crap,
and it's impossible to
find a good map.
Well on the bright side,
I bet there's a way we can
use it to our advantage.
[LEONE]
So... Mine.
Hmm? Uh‐oh, why the
sudden change in tone?
Hehehe!
So like what is the story
on you and Tatsumi?
Ah! Whaaat?!
[LEONE]
Oh come on, you don't think
I wasn't gonna notice.
I mean seriously, you two've
been all cute and awkward
since we left Kyoroku.
Hey now you wait
just a minute!
There's NOTHING going on
between me and that idiot,
are you looking for a punch
in the face or something?!
Aww, it's okay, you don't have
to get all flustered about it!
What?! Whatever, I'm not
getting all flustered!
Well, if that's how you're
gonna be about it...
Then I guess he's
up for grabs then!
Uh?
Oh hell no!
[LEONE]
Hahaha...
Uh, oh...
You are really pathetic.
That's adorable, but I'm still
taking Tatsumi for myself!
Errr...
Hmph!
Quit screwing around and
get back to work!
Let's go!
Not flustered at all.
[NAJENDA]
Got it.
Continue the mission as planned.
Right!
You can count on us.
Apparently we're no longer in
contact with the western tribe.
[AKAME]
Hm? Really?
It's fine.
I was expecting this.
Let's not deviate
from the plan.
When we storm the palace...
I would like the two of you
to take the lead.
Don't fail me!
Understood.
Tatsumi, Lubbock.
Please get through this.
[LUBBOCK] Hey, Tatsumi.
[TATSUMI] Hm?
[LUBBOCK]
What are you gonna do when
the revolution's over?
[TATSUMI]
Uh... hmm... I dunno...
I guess I never really
thought about it.
What about you?
You got plans?
Well, I've been running
that bookstore on the side.
I'll probably just
stick with that.
Maybe I could make it
a national chain
or something.
Wow.
And then!
When the timing's right
I'll ask Najenda to marry me!
Oh, is that so?
That sounds nice.
While we're on the subject,
what's going on with
you and Mine?
Huh?! What does she
have to do with this?!
Aw, don't be shy!
Everybody can tell there's
been a little spark
between the two of
you love birds
ever since we got
back from Kyoroku.
So spill it!
Tell me how far have
you gotten with her.
Ooh, you've at least
landed a smooch, right?
Hey man! Cut it out!
[MAID]
Uh, pardon me...
Huh?
[MAID]
You're uh...
members of Night Raid, right?
Uh...
Ah!
Lemme guess you must be
with the resistance.
I am.
Once we go inside,
we'll have to be very quiet.
Okay.
[LUBBOCK]
I gotta say I'm surprised
a high‐class lady like you
would be part of the resistance.
[MAID]
My father was one of the
Emperor's instructors,
but the Minister accused him
of having ulterior motives
against the Empire.
He threw my father and
my mother in prison.
[LUBBOCK]
Well now I get it.
[TATSUMI]
So that means...
even more people in the palace
must support the revolution.
[MAID]
Yes.
They've united under a group
of anti‐Minister bureaucrats,
who stay in close contact
with the Revolutionary Army.
[LUBBOCK]
And it's up to us
to help those guys
get the revolutionaries gathered
together from the inside,
once the siege on the
palace actually goes down.
[TATSUMI]
Alright. Perfect.
Good to know we're not alone.
[LUBBOCK]
We were chosen over
everyone else for this job
because of my stealth
and your invisibility.
We can't screw up!
Hm.
This is it.
[Knocking]
Huh?
You alright?
Something's wrong.
Whenever I knock twice,
someone's supposed to respond
back with a password knock.
Uh!
[LUBBOCK]
Stand back.
Hm?
Huh?
[Maid shocked]
Whoa..
what happened here?!
This isn't good guys;
they already found the hideout.
Huh?!
[LUBBOCK]
Get out, NOW!
Uuh...
Huh?
Hm!
[SYURA]
Hehe...
Took you long enough;
I've been waiting forever.
Hate to be the one
to break it to you,
but I had to eliminate all those
idiots with the "resistance".
You may call me
the Great Syura!
You two are with
the Night Raid, yes?
You had better be worth
all the trouble.
Huh?
Oh! You must be the little shit
with Genreal Esdeath
when I sent her to that
deserted island or whatever?
[TATSUMI]
So I guess you must've
been responsible for
the Danger Beasts!
Why'd you do it?
Why do anything?
'Cause it's amusing,
young man!
There's nothing in this world
that bothers me more
than being bored.
And those creatures kept me
pretty well entertained.
That's enough... eat this!
[LUBBOCK]
Tatsumi!
Wh... what the?!
[BUDO]
Just as I thought, a few rats
have found their way in.
Uh...
Oh! I'm always up for a
visit from my Uncle Budo.
I'll let you take care of
the pipsqueak.
Exactly what
I had in mind.
I am known as Budo.
His Majesty the Emperor granted
me the title of Great General.
[TATSUMI]
I've heard rumors
about this monster.
You are villainous trash
threatening the Empire...
you are finished.
Now face your judgment.
And feel the Wrath of the
Lightning God Adramelech!
Ah!
Urgh!
Tatsumi!
Ahh!
Uh... How did he
manage to do that?
He never even touched me!
Impressive.
Not many men can
dodge my attack.
I see determination
in your eyes.
Errr..
Incursio!
Be careful with that guy!
Hehehe...
Huh?
Uuh!
Ugh!
Heh!
What?!
How'd you do that?!
I think you're gonna be
a fun one to mess with.
Leave him
to me, guys!
This precious little
victim is all mine.
Err...
[ESDEATH]
I quite enjoyed that.
As one might expect, the
atmosphere of the battlefield
suits me far better
than bodyguard duty.
It's time to return
to the Capital.
It won't be long,
Night Raid.
Hyaa!
[SYURA]
Aw...
What?!
Don't forget to look
behind you, Night Raid!
[Punch]
Ugh!
Well now!
What do we have here?
A seamstress?
[Grunt]
Ooh, don't get
such a pouty face;
I'm about to share
with you a secret.
I call this little
toy "Shambhala."
It gives me the ability to
teleport either myself
or my adversaries...
Huh?!
...to anywhere I've left
my pretty little mark!
Huh?!
He can manipulate space!
But the damn thing
does wear me out.
I couldn't use it
in quick succession
until just recently.
[Spray]
Uhhh...
Then I found this juicy‐stuff
when I got to the Capital.
It really lets me "cut loose",
if you will!
As you can see...
I got a little carried away
and put markers
all over the place!
Huh...
Ah!
What's wrong?
Not gonna run?
[Panting]
Aww, man!
You giving up already?
Hehe...
[LUBBOCK]
Getting away from him
won't do any good!
No matter where I run,
he can warp right up to me!
But...
He can't follow me
somewhere he hasn't marked!
Ha!
Huh?
Ugh!
Aaah... Urg!
Did that get you all pissy?
[SYURA] Awww.
So I guess you can put up
markers in midair can't ya.
[SYURA]
Bingo, smarty pants.
Think I'd leave you
a safe place to hide?
You've nowhere to run!
[Grunts]
[TATSUMI]
He hits hard but his
movements are exaggerated.
I can take him!
Ah!
Hyaa!
Young man, I'm curious
what is your name?
Huh...
Tell me who you are.
Or perhaps assassins like you
don't have names?
It's Tatsumi!
[BUDO]
Tatsumi.
Seems to be a sincere boy;
and honest enough.
And not a hint of hesitation
in his posture.
I can only imagine
the amount of training
it took for him to achieve
this level of skill.
Even so...
Uh!
I am charged with the
termination of any
who mean to bring harm
to his Imperial Majesty!
HAA!
Guh!
[Scream]
[Tatsumi screams]
Tatsumi!
Uh... Huh?
Hey, what're you doing?
[MAID]
I'm sorry!
I have to do this...
Hey!
I have to, for my mother...
and for my father...
[LUBBOCK] Stop it, let me go!
I'm sorry...
[Gasp]
Didn't I tell you
to stay out of this?
[LUBBOCK] Huh...
Stupid toys should not be
interfering with my plans.
She's a... a toy?
Uh‐huh.
Everything from these morons to
the Capital itself, are my toys!
Pretty soon I'll leave
my old man in the dust,
and they'll be
crowning me emperor!
Hey now, don't tell me
you're quitting.
We're only just getting
started, sonny!
No... it's over.
And it looks like you lose.
Huh?
Uh?
Oh...
Owwwww!
Don't move!
Or I'll have to take off
something bigger next time.
Damn you!
Huh? What's this?!
[LUBBOCK]
A barrier of
World‐Severing String.
I'd already used a lot,
but I had just enough left
to pull this together.
[SYURA]
Son of a bitch! You set this up
while you were running!
[LUBBOCK]
You gave me plenty of time.
And all of your bragging
and showing off
gave me a pretty good indication
of where all the markers were.
[SYURA]
You little shit!
Listen up! All of you,
drop your weapons now!
Syura, I've got a few questions
that I need to ask you.
[Stabbed]
Guh!
Uh... You...
Please, Lord Syura...
I did as I was ordered...
now please, release my family...
Hehehe...
No can do, sweetie!
Haha... Sorry to tell you,
but Mommy and Daddy
died a long time ago!
Hahaha....
Okay, Night Raid, I've really
had a marvelous time. But...
It's time we wrapped this up.
I'd like to express
my gratitude
by letting you
see my trump card.
Bon voyage!
You're off to the
ends of the Earth!
[Panic and screams]
[SYURA]
No one's ever made it
back from out there!
You're gonna die alone in the
emptiness of space, Night Raid!
Hahahaha‐
Huh?
No!
That son of a bitch!
Nothing in this world
or the next
could possibly break the
World‐Severing String!
Not even an Imperial Arms
that controls space!
[Syura struggles]
So, here we go again.
God dammit... Ah!
You cannot get away!
Guh! Ohhh!
It's only right that we
finish this fairly.
If I'm going to die, then
you're going down with me.
The hell I am!
I won't allow myself to die
with rabble like you!
I haven't had time to take this
boring bland vanilla nation
and give it the fun it deserves!
Kind of a crazy sentiment...
but believe it or not,
I do think I understand.
No, I'm not supposed to die yet!
I have so much to do!
So you wanna change
the world? Huh?
Course you do.
Everybody wants to
do that, asshole.
[Cough]
But still...
none of that gives you the right
to treat your fellow
human beings
like they're your own
personal playthings
and to treat them like
they're nothing!
[Choke]
Uh...
Thanks for protecting me
so long, Cross Tail.
I'm sorry, Najenda.
This was as far
as I could go.
I'm leaving the rest
to you, Tatsumi.
Uh...
[Gasp]
Oh, Lubb...
[TATSUMI]
Aaaugh!
[Sniffling]
He's dead!
[Crying]
Noooo!
How could you leave me?!
Oh well!
Can't change anything
by grieving over the
fallen, can we?
Well he did manage to eliminate
a Night Raid assassin.
Rather fair trade if you ask me.
[BUDO]
I took the liberty of confining
the other Night Raid member
to the dungeon.
[MINISTER]
Excellent work.
Let's see... now...
If we wish to subdue the rebels,
I imagine we need to make
an example of that boy.
It must be bold.
So I wonder what's the best form
of torture to make a point.
Hmm... You're still as depraved
as ever, aren't you, Minister?
Listen. Punishing a rebel calls
for a higher grade of cruelty.
I have a few suggestions...
[Door opens]
Hm?
I couldn't help but overhear
your conversation.
And if I may, I'd like
that job to be mine.
Ohh?
Tatsumi, I won't let anyone
take you from me!
[Bell rings]
An execution? Oh no...
Uh! Oh God... no...
[Music playing]