But why? Why would you allow
them to die just to save me?
[NAJENDA]
Get over yourself.
Huh?
If we hadn't stopped
that execution
it would've seriously damaged
the Revolutionary Army's morale.
Besides, everyone participated
of their own free will.
Yeah, well that's
not the point.
[Blow]
Furthermore...
we managed to eliminate
a long‐standing obstacle when
we killed Great General Budo.
We've gained a lot
from this mission.
Uh! Is that all that
matters to you?!
Tatsumi, you do realize this
whole thing's been hard
on the Boss too, right?
She lost Susanoo.
[Blow]
These things happen.
It was doing its job as
a weapon, that's all.
Poor Su.
As the living it is
our responsibility
to carry out the wishes
of the ones who are gone.
[TATSUMI]
I don't know if I can.
It may be heavy,
but it's a burden
that none of us have
the right to abandon.
Akame...
In other words,
if we quit now...
then all the dead will
have died for nothing!
Yeah, you're right!
I guess somebody has to put
an end to all this sadness.
[NAJENDA]
In order to use his trump card,
Susanoo needed to take my life.
But I'm still here...
Susanoo, did you burn through
your own life energy
to keep from killing me?
[Blow]
You were never just
an Imperial Arms.
You were an irreplaceable...
companion.
[TATSUMI]
Do you...
remember what you told me?
You said that you were gonna
make something of your life
and rid this world
of intolerance.
I'll do it, Mine.
I'll make your wish come true.
I promise.
[Crowd rioting]
Lemme go!
Keep up this rebellious crap
and I'll put you under arrest!
This place is a joke;
can't you see it's
falling apart around us!
[Guard]
What was that?!
No! Don't!
Hm...
[WAVE]
Hmph!
How much longer do we
have to put up with this?!
It'll be over soon.
The Empire's
on its way down.
Most of the people we were
supposed to protect
are now siding
with the Revolution.
Is there still a place
for us here anymore?
Try to stay calm.
The chaos probably won't stop
even after the revolution.
And when the time comes,
the people are going
to need our help.
It kinda sounds like you
knew this would happen.
Well, it came a little
earlier than I thought
it would.
Huh?
I was desperately
hoping for reform.
That's why I joined
the Jaegers,
to try to make a difference in
this nation from the inside.
To make a difference?
This Empire has
become corrupt.
That said, I think this kind of
rebellion is unacceptable.
So you chose to work
under General Esdeath.
Yes.
I actually find her
quite fascinating.
You are a strange guy
y'know that.
Hm... I get that a lot.
Y'know my initial
intention for joining
was to rise up in the ranks,
but I got sidetracked.
Because I've enjoyed my time
with everyone here so much.
Speaking of which, Kurome,
what are you planning on doing?
Since you've got
one foot in the grave.
Huh? Wait a minute,
how did you find out
about Kurome?!
You shouldn't be
all that surprised, Wave.
It's obvious by the way
you've been acting.
Ah!
At this point,
you could probably be
free from the Jaegers
without becoming a
target, yourself.
Be free?
Yes.
I don't have any need for
a brief taste of freedom.
There's only one thing
I care about in this world.
Aah!
Ugh!
Now this is the kind of battle
I enjoy the most!
If any of you neophytes are
unsatisfied with your destiny,
I invite you to put me
in my place!
You can go to Hell!
As soon as you're dead this
corrupt nation is finished!
[ESDEATH]
Oh, an Imperial Arms?
How cute.
Aah!
Is there not a single one
of you who can challenge me?
[Crowd in fear]
Tatsumi escaped certain death
against unbelievable odds.
We're simply meant
to be together.
[Crowd charges]
Wait for me, my love.
I'm coming for you.
Once I've cleaned up this mess.
[MESSENGER]
The Imperial Capital is almost
completely surrounded now!
What the hell is
going on out there?!
Not even General Esdeath
is capable of leading an army
in every direction
at the same time!
[Footsteps]
Your Highness!
The Empire is crumbling
under our reign...
have we not been good rulers?
[MINISTER]
There's nothing wrong with
your rule, Your Majesty.
Oh, Minister Honest!
You idiots should be
more supportive.
They've let their fear
get the best of them.
I hate to say it, but I
am painfully aware of your
feelings on this matter.
These men are fools!
They don't understand
all the strides
you've taken
to keep our land peaceful.
The citizens have
started to rebel
against us.
Please tell me
what we should do!
There comes a time
when a nation's ruler
is called to show his leadership
with an iron fist.
You must make your authority
known to your people!
Show your strength!
Huh?
It couldn't be...
[MINISTER]
Now they'll see
the Emperor's power...
[Cough]
I don't... have much time.
So... let's finish this...
Big Sister.
[Caw]
[CIVILIAN]
Revolutionary spies.
[ANOTHER CIVILIAN]
I take it this is a warning.
I cannot believe
what I'm seeing.
Huh?! It's a message for me.
Huh? It's a message?
I'm being challenged
to a duel.
Uh? What does it say?
"Come to the Kadai Forest
Institution ruins."
[TATSUMI]
This is stupid!
You know it's a trap!
If it was a trap they
wouldn't have waited
this long to come for me.
It's a personal grudge.
A grudge?
Then who is it?
Kurome's ready to
settle things between us.
Uh!
Does it have to be right now?
Is this fight really all that
important to you two?
Mm‐hm.
Akame I'm sure you know
that the lives of
thousands of people are
resting on our shoulders!
How can you put this
personal vendetta
over everything else?
That's exactly why
I have to do this.
No matter what, I can't
ignore Kurome's feelings.
She's the enemy.
She's my sister.
Hm.
I'm the only person she knows
who can truly understand...
what she's going through.
If you say so.
But I'm coming too.
You can't.
The revolution is
going to need
every bit of your strength
for the final siege.
Do not forget what
your mission is.
Okay fine, but promise me
you'll come back alive.
Tatsumi, please.
That's what you're always
telling me to do.
So I expect the same
thing from you.
Fine... you have my word.
[Footsteps]
I knew you'd show up...
Akame.
Hello Kurome.
You wanna snack?
Hm.
You remember this place,
don't you?
This isn't the first time
we've met here.
It's also the place...
where you turned
your back on us.
Seems like the perfect place
for me to kill you.
It sure takes me back.
No matter what
happened to us,
you were always right there
looking out for me.
We didn't have anyone
but each other,
and this was the only
place we felt needed.
They trained us to be
assassins for the Empire.
We learned to stop uprisings
before they started.
That was the way we were
taught to protect the peace.
Under orders,
we learned to kill
anyone who might be
a threat to the Empire.
As far as we knew,
we were doing the right thing.
Big Sister! Haha!
Kurome.
I missed you.
[AKAME]
After being raised in
two different squads,
we finally got the chance
to be together again.
You came as a replacement for
someone who'd been killed.
[KUROME]
After that, the two of us
were inseparable...
like we were trying to
make up for all the time
we'd been apart.
We were the ultimate team.
Some of our missions
were difficult,
but I made it through
because I had you.
If you were with me,
I was happy.
But... then...
[Panting]
But then you betrayed the Empire
and joined Night Raid.
Why?! I tried so hard
to stop you!
Being abandoned
by my own sister
absolutely crushed me.
Every day
since you left,
I've been imagining more
and more ways to kill you.
Is killing me gonna
solve your problems?
There is no solution.
However, if I kill you...
then you can be beside me
for all eternity.
[Kurome coughs]
[AKAME]
Using an Imperial Arms
is very strenuous.
It must be unbearable
when you're so weak.
I can end your suffering.
Haha! Sister, it's time for us
to fight... to the death.
[WAVE]
Kurome.
[RUN]
I guess she's gone.
She needed to take
care of some
unfinished business.
But why would she
leave without saying
anything about it?
If she'd said something,
you would have tried
to stop her.
Do you have any idea
where she could've gone?
Maybe a place that's
important to the two of them?
Uh... Ah...
Uh...
Why did you have to leave
and betray the squad?
Everything would have
been fine between us
if you hadn't run away!
I learned a lot
about life from
going on my own.
And I realized that we were
never fighting for the
good of the nation!
We were only doing
the Empire's dirty work!
Murdering people
without question!
The way things stand,
no good is ever going to
come from this government.
It's why I wanted you
to leave with me.
How could you expect
me to do that
when so many others
were forced to die
for the sake of
their missions?!
All that sadness was caused by
the leaders of the Empire!
If we can bring happiness
to people by overthrowing
the leadership,
I know our comrades
would understand!
That's a selfish excuse!
[Growls]
Huh?
[Roars]
Danger Beast.
It must've come
out of hiding
when it sensed
our desire to fight!
[Roar]
Kurome!
Ah!
Uhh...
Natara!
[Grunts]
[Growls]
You will pay for
hurting my friends!
Doya!
[Roar]
Uh!
No!
[Grunt]
Alright that's it!
I don't have any more
time to waste on you!
[Growl]
Aah!
Uh!
[Growl]
[Gasp]
That was really close.
Are you okay?
Akame.
Let's go get him.
Hm.
Hyaaa!
[Groan]
[Gas venting]
[Groans]
[Roar]
You're done!
[Groans]
[KUROME]
Haha...
Looks like you and I
still have what it takes.
The two of us always were
pretty good at this weren't we?
You remember don't you,
Big Sister?!
[KUROME]
Haha...
Ah!
Ha!
[Grunt]
Get her!
Uh! I should've known
my pawns couldn't handle it.
This battle... IS OVER!
[Explosive impact]
[WAVE]
I won't let you hurt Kurome!
Wave?!
C'mon, Night Raid,
I'm your target now!
Ugh!
What the?!
[WAVE]
Move, Tatsumi!
[KUROME]
You move, Wave!
Huh?
But you're my teammate;
I can't just walk
away from you!
But I want you to.
Kurome...
What are you doing
here, Tatsumi?!
I came to make sure no one
interferes with your fight.
Huh?
Hm.
[WAVE]
Tatsumi, we don't
have time for this!
[TATSUMI]
I wish I could stop them too!
But if I did that,
then they'd never
be able to finally sort
this thing out!
[WAVE]
Is this how Night Raid assassins
settle their differences?!
I cannot allow it to happen!
[TATSUMI]
This a matter of the heart!
Sometimes there are
problems that can only
be solved by yourself...
without any help!
[KUROME]
A matter of the heart?
[WAVE]
I...
[KUROME]
Wave.
Uh...
Thank you for coming to help me.
Maybe if things had
gone differently...
The two of us could've
been friends or something.
But Kurome...
It's time for us
to finally deal
with all the regret
and pain we've had
for so long.
It's time
to end this.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Kurome...
my little sister.
Mmhmm.
You know I've always
loved you, Big Sister.
Ugh!
Hyaaa!
This couldn't be
the only way
for them to resolve
their differences.
[Wave crying]
I wasn't able to help her...
I couldn't do
anything to stop it!
You came to look after
my little sister.
That's enough.
Uhh...
[WAVE]
No... no...
Damn it!
I don't understand.
I don't know why...
why we're even fighting
each other anymore.
If you can't find
a reason to fight
then you shouldn't
be fighting.
Only those who fully
comprehend the
implications of war
can be capable of
bearing arms.
Implications?
You'll bear this weight
for the rest of your life.
Aaah...
Uh, Akame!
Didn't I tell you
to stay back?
Yeah, maybe
during the fight.
But you never said anything
about coming to take care of
an injured companion,
now did you?
Huh?
I've said goodbye to so many
of my friends along the way.
But that's nothing...
compared to all the loss you've
been through your whole life.
I couldn't even begin to
comprehend your pain.
Huh!
Akame...
you're not gonna lose
any more loved ones.
Ever again.
[Akame crying]
[MINISTER]
I'm so pleased you
came to this decision!
What a wise ruler you are!
Now, open your Imperial Arms
passed down through
generations of royalty!
Those insufferable
revolutionaries...
as well as the
brainless masses...
soon they'll know
your supremacy!
This is our Empire.
We must use our powers
to defend this land.
[Music playing]