[SAYO]
Let's make a pact, that when
we die, we die together!
[IEYASU]
We're gonna be leaders in
the Imperial Capital!
[TATSUMI]
And make enough money to save
the village! We'll be heroes!
So much for that.
Now I'm out here all alone.
Huh?
Hehehe...
Whoa! Don't sneak up
on me like that!
So, have you decided to
officially join yet?
I told you guys‐
You really do have the makings
of an assassin, you know!
It's not a matter of whether or
not I'd be good at it, alright.
I just don't...
wanna kill people.
Well, I'm gonna introduce you
to the guys anyway!
Let me go! Agh! My neck!
Oh? He still doesn't want to
be part of the team in spite
of all that's happened?
He's a bit hesitant.
So I was hoping maybe you
could give him a few words
of encouragement, okay?
Hmm...
Well, since we showed you the
location of our hideout...
if we can't convince you to join
the team, then you'll be dead.
Uh, is that supposed to be
encouragement or a threat?
Just give it plenty of
thought, okay?
Huh? "Mend Your Airheaded Ways"?
Oh my god these guys are
a bunch of circus freaks.
[MINE]
What the hell?
Hmm?
Leone! Why'd you bring this
loser back to the hideout?
He's one of us now.
And did no one think to
ask for MY opinion?
[TATSUMI]
Uh... Okay.
I won't allow it.
It's obvious you're not
cut from the same professional
cloth as the rest of the group.
I mean, just look at you.
Wha‐?! What's that
supposed to mean?!
[LEONE]
Aw, don't let it get to you;
that's Mine's way of
saying hello.
Hmph!
This is our practice field where
we go to let off some steam.
Oh! And look who's already out
here trying to work up a sweat.
That's Bulat.
Hyaaaaa!
Incredible. He's really
good with that spear.
[Grunting]
Oh...
Hey! Oh!
Aren't you the fella we
picked up the other day?
Wait, how do you know
about that?
Huh? Oh... I should've known you
wouldn't recognize me like this.
I was wearing my armor
the first time we met.
Uh... Oh!
Name's Bulat.
Pleasure's mine.
Uh... hi there.
And yes he's gay.
Geh!
Haha...
Now don't give him the
wrong idea...
Yet.
I can think of a lot
of wrong ideas.
[LUBBOCK]
Hehe... It's almost time
for Leone's bath.
I'd do just about anything
for a sneak peek at that
smokin' hot body!
[LEONE]
In that case...
‐Huh?
‐How about you give up
two fingers?
[Gasps]
[Screams]
[LEONE]
You never learn, do you?
[LUBBOCK]
Owowowowow!
[LEONE]
Next time I'll break your arm.
‐Owww!
‐This is Lubbock.
As you can see, he's an idiot.
[LEONE]
Let's see, who's next?
[TATSUMI]
I don't know how many
more I can take.
Hehe. The next one's a cutie,
so try not to stare.
She's stuffing her face
over there by the fire.
[LEONE]
Hey, Akame!
‐Hm?
[TATSUMI]
‐And there's this freak!
I'm just now realizing she's
eating a giant bird.
Did she kill that
thing herself?!
[LEONE]
Akame's our resident wild child.
Leone, have some.
Huh? Thanks!
[AKAME]
Well? Have you joined us yet?
Uh, no...
Then I'm sorry but I won't
be sharing any of my
dinner with you.
I'm okay with that!
This chick's already tried
to kill me twice.
I'd better watch out for her.
Is it just me or is everyone
a little extra jacked up today?
That's 'cause the boss is back.
Uh? The boss?
‐Boss!
‐Hey!
Welcome back!
Did you bring me anything good?
[NAJENDA]
Now why would I do that?
About one of your most
recent assignments...
I was told you completed it
three days overdue.
Ah, crap!
[Whining]
When facing a powerful opponent,
it's unwise to get caught up
in the fun.
Shouldn't you know better
than that by now?
[LEONE]
Okay, I've learned my lesson,
now please let go of me!
Anyway. Tell me about the boy.
Oh! That's right!
He's going to be joining us.
I haven't agreed to anything!
Does he seem promising?
Absolutely.
See? All we want you
to do is try. 'Kay?
S'not what you said before!
Akame, go get everyone together.
I want to hear about everything,
including that boy.
Thank you all. I think I
understand the situation here.
Tatsumi! How would you like
to be the newest member
of Night Raid?
You're gonna kill me if I
refuse to join, right.
[NAJENDA]
No, we won't KILL you.
‐Huh?
[NAJENDA]
‐But we wouldn't
let you leave, either.
You'd have to remain here
and work in our factory.
Either way, we won't
take your life,
but I do encourage you to join.
Your choice.
I, uh...
I just wanted to make a lot of
money in the Imperial Capital
so that I'd be able to save
my village from starvation.
But the Capital wasn't
what I thought.
[BULAT]
‐Tatsumi.
‐Huh?
Corruption in the Capital
is creating mass‐poverty
all over the countryside.
Don't you want to uproot all
that corruption at the source?
Like a man would?
Bulat used to be a high‐ranking
officer in the Imperial Army,
but he joined us when he
realized what was really
going on in the Capital.
If we don't do something
about the scum terrorizing
the Capital,
then it's never gonna
get cleaned up.
So it's our job to take out
those bastards whenever
we get the chance.
That's fine...
But I don't think you can make
a real big difference
by just eliminating a couple
of rotten eggs here and there.
I mean, doing things this
way won't save places
like my village.
That's correct.
And that's exactly why Night
Raid's the perfect fit for you.
[TATSUMI]
Uh... why is that?
[NAJENDA]
There's an anti‐Empire group
called the Revolutionary Army
that has a hideout
south of the Capital.
A whole army?
They started out small,
but they've grown in to a
rather formidable organization.
They needed a separate unit to
specialize in covert operations,
such as recon and
assassinating targets.
That's why they created
Night Raid!
We're only putting out one fire
at a time right now...
but when the Revolutionary Army
decides to make its move...
amidst the chaos we'll head
straight for the cause
of this mess...
the Minister!
So you're gonna... kill him?
Only then will our nation
truly see change.
So if our nation had
a new start...
you really think all of
the people would be safe
and happy again?
[NAJENDA]
I am certain.
[TATSUMI]
I... I love it.
It's like you guys are
taking out the trash...
killing off the
bad guys one by one.
You're a rogue team of assassins
for the sake of justice!
[Others burst out laughing]
Huh? What'd I say?!
Why's everyone laughing?
Tatsumi, no matter how
you describe it,
we're still murderers.
And there's no justice to be
found in the way we do things.
Any given moment...
every one of us could be forced
to atone for the blood
that we've spilled.
Man! He has no idea.
It'll be a thousand years
before he can handle it.
Hold on.
Uh?
I, uh...
Every team member fights
for a different reason,
but each bares
a strong resolve.
Are you prepared
to risk your life?
You guys are gonna pay me
for this, aren't you?
Yes. And if you work
hard enough,
I think you'll make more than
enough to save your village.
Then I wanna do it!
Please allow me to be
part of Night Raid!
You probably won't be going back
to them as some hero, you know.
I know. But that doesn't matter
to me as long as they'll
be taken care of.
Hmph.
Works for me.
Prepare yourself for a life
unlike any other.
Welcome to Night Raid.
You're dismissed for the night.
Akame...
Hm?
You're in charge of
training him for now.
Ugh?
If he becomes a nuisance,
feel free to kill him.
No problem.
No problem?!
Better do a good job
if you wanna live!
Uh...
[TATSUMI]
It HAD to be her...
I am so dead.
The more skills we can start
learning right now
the quicker we'll be able to
get ahead in the military!
And if we ever run out of
provisions or something,
maybe knowing how to prepare
food might actually
save us someday.
Sayo... Ieyasu...
Who knew learning to cook
with you guys would
come in so handy?
[MINE]
I said I want seconds!
‐Oh! Me too!
‐I'll take some!
Oh yes if you don't mind!
They're running me ragged!
Come on...
I thought I was supposed
to become an assassin,
not a stupid chef!
Don't look at me.
I just put food on
the plates. M'kay?
Oh, so they won't let you cook
because you kept sampling
the food, is that it?
I don't know what you mean.
You are not a very good liar.
[MINE]
Aww, look, you're right at
home in the kitchen,
aren't you, rookie?
What?!
Later, Sunshine!
Bulat?
Wait a sec...
are you guys heading out
on a mission?
Yeah, this one's a
special request.
Shouldn't I come too?
You stay here in the kitchen!
Now you be a good cook and
chop a few cucumbers for me.
Why does she always
have to be like that?
[Mine mocking laughter]
See ya!
Grrr...
Wow, this place is great!
Today we'll start by
catching fish for dinner.
Whoa!
What seems to be the problem?
Thank god it's just a swimsuit.
The target is Koga Tuna.
See how many you can get.
Aren't those things extremely
rare and stupidly hard to
get a hold of?
Wha‐?
First you have to swim all
the way down to the bottom.
Then conceal your aura
and make your attack.
You have to act very quickly.
Give it a try.
Hmm... Whatever you say!
Wow. So in the end our
little Tatsumi caught
two whole fish, huh?
Akame said you ripped off
your shirt and said some
shit like "I got this!"
This'll take some time.
[TATSUMI]
Man... why the hell would she
say something like that?
I can't stand her.
Anyway Leone.
What did you find out?
Here's the deal. The targets are
Ogre of the Imperial Guard
and Gamal the Oil Merchant.
And according to the client...
[CLIENT]
Ogre has been accepting
bribes from an oil merchant
named Gamal.
So whenever he manages to get
himself into trouble...
Ogre finds a way to pin all of
the blame on someone else.
My fiancé fell victim to this.
And he was sentenced to death.
Please... I'm begging you,
you must do something.
[LEONE]
Understood. That son of a bitch
will get what he deserves.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Here it is.
She paid it all up front.
I'm amazed she could
give us that much.
She smelled sickly.
I think she's been
selling her body.
Huh? Is that right?
[NAJENDA]
Sure she's not lying?
My senses have never
steered me wrong yet, Boss..
He's guilty.
Hmm. Then Night Raid
accepts this assignment.
In the new nation
we wish to create..
S'no room for his trash.
He needs divine punishment.
We shouldn't have too much
trouble with the oil merchant,
but I betcha Ogre'll be
a pain in the ass.
Ogre is a demon.
He's very skilled with a sword,
even the hit men are
scared of him.
And he's always surrounded by
a huge crowd of subordinates,
he's never seen alone.
He's so careful that Gamal
delivers all payments to
his personal chambers.
But on his days off he goes
drinking on Main Street,
right by the palace.
[TATSUMI]
Okay. Sounds like we know when
we'll have to strike.
[NAJENDA]
But, that area is
heavily guarded.
We can't send Akame;
they already know
what she looks like.
Hellooo! They don't have any
wanted posters of me yet!
Can you do it?
Targets like these pukes
are the ones I live for.
I think we should wait
'til the others are here.
But at the moment we still
have no idea when they're
coming back, am I right?
Fine! Then I say we set out on
this mission without 'em!
Oh? You think you're capable
of killing Ogre yourself?
‐What?
‐Careful how you answer that!
Keep pretending you're a bigshot
and we might just make you
back it up!
Oh!
As you are now, you can't do it.
Wha‐?!
But I'm an expert swordsman!
[AKAME]
What I mean is that you
can't kill people.
Uh... I did it once.
You were blinded by rage
that night.
Can you kill a person
under any circumstances
without stopping
to think about it?
I don't know, but what if
Ogre is framing another
innocent person
while the four of us are
sitting here arguing about it?!
That's why I don't
want us to wait!
I know how much it hurts to lose
someone for no good reason.
And it's not fun!
I don't want anyone else to
have to feel like that!
Then it's settled.
I admire your
conviction, Tatsumi.
Take him down.
Now that's what I like to hear!
You've got spunk, dontcha?!
I'd like you two ladies to
focus on the oil merchant.
You got it!
Understood.
See Akame, I can take care
of business when push
comes to shove.
I'll withhold judgement
of your ability
until you complete the mission
and report back.
If you begin with
over‐confidence and arrogance...
you'll die.
Uh!
She'll change her tune.
I just have to prove myself
by killing Ogre.
This is Main Street.
Did you memorize the map
like I told you?
Yeah. Yeah I got it.
If you begin with
over‐confidence and arrogance...
you'll die.
Tatsumi, I think I should
tell you a few things
about Akame's past.
When she was a kid, she and her
sister were sold to the Empire.
They were placed in an assassin
training camp with other
abandoned kids.
She learned how to survive
the harsh surroundings
as well as the art of murder.
She grew up an assassin, blindly
doing the Empire's dirty work.
But as Akame got older,
she started to see the darkness
the Empire was hiding.
One day, she was sent to kill ‐
the Boss. But it didn't happen.
Somehow, she convinced her to
join the Revolutionary Army.
And join the side of the people.
But, by the time she
could do it,
most of the kids she had
grown up with were already dead.
Do you see what I'm
getting at Tatsumi?
Yeah yeah, as a
professional killer,
you're saying there are things
a rookie like me doesn't
understand yet.
Well, if you manage to
live through today,
then you'll know a little more.
Whooo! That bathroom
will never be the same.
Anyway,time to get back
to living the dream!
[LEONE]
Wait a second.
I've got a better idea.
Killed by two hot babes,
you lucky dog!
Now then, I wonder how the
newb's doing with his
part of the job?
Ahhh. Nothing like finishing off
a long day of torture than
knocking back a cold one.
Excuse me, Master Ogre.
Uh‐huh?
I have a matter of
utmost importance
I'd like to
discuss with you.
That so?
Let's hear it.
We need to speak privately.
Huh?
This kid doesn't have an aura.
Alright start talkin'.
I wanna get home.
Of course.
Sayo, Ieyasu,
please watch over me.
Huh?
Please, sir, I beg you to
let me join the Imperial Guard!
I have to earn money to
send back to my family
in the country!
Uh... I shoulda known
it was something like that.
Follow the procedures like
everyone else, jackass.
I tried,
but they wouldn't
even take my application.
That's not my problem.
It's not my fault you're
a puny little weakling!
That was quick!
He acted without fear.
Been awhile since
somebody defied me.
[Groan]
Just like that!
I'll withhold judgement
of your ability
until you complete the mission
and report back.
Oh! That's right.
I better be getting back
to base now.
[Growling]
Huh?
Ah!
Uh!
Did you really think you could
slay the mighty Ogre?!
A pathetic little snot‐nosed
brat like you?
Ugh!
Okay, lemme guess.
You're one of those
Night Raid punks
that goes around killing all
the people in power, right?
The weak can squeal
all they want,
but the strong will always
rule in this Empire, boy!
Who you deem worthy
means nothing!
I judge the fate of the people!
I won't let you kill
anyone else!
[Roar]
On whose order have you
come to me, boy?!
The fiancée of the little worm
I just had executed?
Guess I was right!
I told myself I shoulda
knocked off that wench
while I had the chance!
Well, I still could if
I really wanted to.
First thing I'll do is
chase that bitch down.
I'll find everyone she knows,
bring 'em up on charges
and take my time torturing them
to death while she watches!
But not until I kill you first!
[Gasp]
These guys are all the same.
They throw their weight around
and use their power for
nothing but evil.
I want nothing more than
to take scum like him...
and slash it...
to pieces!
[Groaning]
You've defeated a powerful
adversary on your own.
I'm impressed.
Yep!
Hear that, Akame?
I did exactly what
you wanted me to,
AND I came out without
a scratch on me!
Now, tell me how wonderful I am!
Hmm?
Ah!
What the hell are you
doing to me?!
Leone, Boss, grab him.
Ah!
Uhhmm...
Thank goodness.
Oh...
I've seen people die from
infection because they were too
proud to report their wounds.
It's good you didn't get hurt.
It's hard for most people
to survive past their
first mission.
I'm glad you survived.
Uh... Hm.
The only reason Akame was
so hard on you before
was because she was worried
about your safety.
Learning to cook helped with
your communication.
And hunting taught you
basic killing techniques.
Do you not realize everything
we made you do was for a
very specific reason?
Oh, uh, I guess not.
Sorry Akame. I got...
I got the wrong idea.
‐It's okay.
‐Huh?
Just try to keep coming back
alive, Tatsumi.
Sure! S'long as you keep
looking after me, Akame.
[Giggles]
Oh my god this is so
adorable and cheesy
and the fact that you're
almost naked makes it
even more ridiculous.
Hey, you're the ones who
took my shirt off!
Well, you're working with Mine
on your next assignment
so I expect your best.
‐Ugh!
Yeouch,
out of the frying pan,
and into the fire!
Ah!
[TATSUMI]
She's even worse!
[Shivers]
I have a bad feeling
all of a sudden.
[Music playing]