I am gonna get a ton of
experience points for this guy!
Behind you!
Ugh!
Uh!
[Gasps]
[TATSUMI]
He slaughtered the big guy
and got the other two
off his back.
And... he did it in
a split second!
[LIVER]
You played a vital role in
getting rid of covert operatives
back then, did you not?
It truly has been a while,
hasn't it, Bulat?
[BULAT]
It's you, General Liver!
[LIVER]
Former General, actually.
Ever since Master Esdeath
saved my life.
I have been her devoted servant.
[TATSUMI]
Huh?
Is this the same guy Bro
was talking about
in the story from his past?
[BULAT]
If things were different, I'd be
drinking a toast to our reunion.
But since they're not,
I'm going to have to kill you.
The mission comes first!
I couldn't have said it
better myself.
General Esdeath's wishes
will be realized.
And to ensure that
I am successful,
she gave me this Imperial Arms!
The Black Marlin,
it's a ring‐type weapon.
It was crafted from the
organs of aquatic Danger Beasts
with the power to control water.
As such, whoever wears it can
manipulate any liquid at will.
If this is our battlefield,
Lady Luck is certainly
smiling upon me.
[BULAT]
So you fight with water now.
Rather convenient that your
boss is an ice user.
[LIVER]
General Esdeath can create
ice out of thin air.
Do not elevate me to her level.
She is a god!
Water Fire!
Touchy, touchy...
[Grunts]
Son of a bitch...
And it looks like Liver's
got his hands full
with this guy, too.
Well, with all this water
around, I'm sure he
should be okay.
But a little backup
would be nice.
[TATSUMI]
Not if I can help it!
Aah!
You guys are frickin' crazy
if you think I'm just gonna
sit over there
and watch the whole time!
You're in the way.
Back off!
You Night Raid people are
really freakin' annoying!
[Grunts]
Uh!
Hehehe...
Ah!
Huh?
Heh...
Ahh!
Uh!
[TATSUMI]
Damn, this kid is fast!
Hehe...
But I've trained for this.
Akame is faster than you!
What?
Do not compare me to
some assassin!
[Panting]
[NYAU]
If he hadn't gotten in
one lucky hit,
I'd have killed him already!
[TATSUMI]
How's he fighting like this
when he's injured?
These Three Beasts are so tough
they make guys like Ogre
look like child's play.
[Growling]
Whoa! The fight's starting to
get pretty intense over there!
Of course!
But it's a battle near
a body of water.
Sir Liver has the advantage!
Ha! Bro's about to mop the floor
with that old geezer.
Liver shall prevail!
He doesn't stand a chance!
The water pressure
will destroy you!
Say goodbye, Bulat!
[Roaring]
[LIVER]
Snake from the Abyss!
[Roar]
Ahhh!
[LIVER]
Hehehe...
It seems I correctly assumed
you would attack the snake
head‐on rather than dodge.
You knew there'd be
countless casualties
if I destroyed the ship.
And perhaps, you'd be able to
avoid my next technique
if your feet were planted
securely on the deck,
but you can't dodge in midair!
[LIVER]
Dark Water Spears!
[BULAT]
Gah!
Aah!
Takes more than a
splash of water
to extinguish the fire
in my soul!
[LIVER]
But of course.
I would never finish you off
with such a simple strike.
After all, I know what
you're capable of.
The two of us have been
through many a battle
together, remember?
I know all your strengths
and weaknesses
better than anyone else
in the world.
And that's precisely why
I'd like to show you
the power of my trump card!
Water Dragons...
Conquer Heaven!
[Roaring]
[BULAT]
Gah!
Aaaaah!
Hmm, I think I got him.
Huh?
[BULAT]
I can't believe you
actually just said that.
You should know better old man!
How did you survive that?!
Haaaa!
[Grunt]
Ah!
Huh?
Ha!
Ugh!
What a joke.
You realize what
you've done, right?
You just threw away your only
chance at defeating Liver.
[TATSUMI]
Bro...
[BULAT]
Tatsumi!
I'm sorry,
it's my fault.
I wasn't able to
hold him off long enough
for you to finish.
What is this?
You mean you can still move.
Why don't you just take
yourself a little nap,
so I can take my precious
time with you later?
[BULAT]
Don't sweat it, okay?
Huh?
I'm just amazed you managed
to get through all this
without an Imperial Arms.
Uh, yeah, I guess...
Even with his armor,
he got beat up pretty bad!
I noticed your Imperial Arms
deactivates itself
after you've taken a certain
amount of damage.
We seem to have
a clear winner.
Hmm. You don't need
to play it tough.
That little drop of blood
coming from your ear
is a dead giveaway.
Uh?
[BULAT]
Your internal organs
must've taken a huge hit
when you used
your trump card.
So I doubt you're in any
condition to use your
Imperial Arms anymore.
Hmph.
Nothing gets past you, does it?
And here I was hoping to
have the upper hand
in the negotiations.
Well then! I must ask.
How would you like to become
a member of Esdeath's army?
I'm sure she would be willing to
bring you on as a Lieutenant.
Thanks, but I lost interest
in serving the Empire
a long time ago.
Don't think of it that way.
You'd be working for
Esdeath, not the Empire.
Doing so changed my life
for the better.
Since joining forces
with Esdeath,
people everywhere
cower before me.
In fact, my name is so feared
that all the bureaucrats
in the Capital
clamour to stay in
my good graces!
I've got every single one
of them under my thumb!
I emplore you to come with me!
If you do, the Master can erase
all of your crimes from
the record books!
I said no.
[BULAT]
Don't you get it.
I would find no joy
in becoming
the very thing we were
sworn to destroy.
Since I know Esdeath is
scratching the Minister's back.
How could I possibly
live with myself.
It'd tarnish my image
as a hero to the masses,
now wouldn't it?
A hero to the masses?
I can't believe a known assassin
would dare to say
something so arrogant.
I was trying to make it sound
like I was being modest.
[NYAU]
Both of them have finally
reached their limit.
But what they don't know
is that we still have
our trump card...
then it's over!
Ah, Bro, wait...
[TATSUMI]
When Imperial Arms
users face off...
one of them always dies.
Neither one of us can use
our weapons anymore.
Then we'll finish this
with our swords.
Ugh.
Huh?
[Grunting]
It's time for a
little enhancement.
I am about to
fight YOU after all.
Bro. Wait a sec!
Something's not right
about this guy!
Yeah, I'm painfully aware
he's not gonna be an
easy one to beat.
[Click]
Here we go!
[Grunt]
[Swords clashing
and battle cries]
Ah!
Uh ah!
That's crazy...
it's hard to believe these two
are both already injured.
[Screams]
Huh?
[Grunts]
[Screams]
Ahhh!
Gak!
You got him!
Argh!
Ha!
Uh?
My real trump card,
Killer Blood Swords!
[BULAT]
Of course you had something
up your sleeve!
Keep after him!
[Scream]
Aaah!
[BULAT]
Ugh!
Bro, you sure you're
gonna be okay?
I don't think I let him
land any fatal blows,
so I should be alright.
I put all I had left
into that final attack...
and yet you still blocked it.
Well played.
If I had hesitated
just a second,
he would have annihilated me
before I knew what hit me.
When I saw the spray pattern
of his blood,
I realized it was
another form of liquid.
You were incredible, Bro!
[TATSUMI]
I can't believe he was able
to wipe out two powerful
enemies...
even though all I did
was get in the way!
Man, that was a
really close call!
[LIVER]
Bulat...
Huh?
There's one thing
I wanted to tell you.
There's a reason I decided to
join General Esdeath's army.
I didn't tell you before.
It's a shame to allow a treasure
like you to rot away in a cell.
I'm looking for an adjutant with
incomparable combat abilities.
I'd like you in my army.
[LIVER]
Huh?
No, I couldn't return to the
army even if I wanted to.
I'm charged with an offense.
Excuses are for the weak.
You may re‐enlist...
because I WANT you to re‐enlist.
To put it frankly,
I will not allow anyone
to raise an objection.
But the Minister will
never stand for it.
[ESDEATH]
I'm a great deal of help
to the Minister.
If you're an asset to my forces,
he'll be glad to have you back.
Please say you'll fight
with me, Liver.
And if you're still
feeling unsure,
allow me to ease your fears.
I have respect and
admiration for Esdeath.
That's the real reason.
Liver...
And as such...
I swear on my honor as a devout
servant of General Esdeath
that in mere moments I will be
taking your life as well!
[Bulat coughs]
Hang in there!
[BULAT]
Ugh... Uh...
That wasn't just an enhancement.
You injected poison
into your own blood!
[TATSUMI]
Uh...
You haven't developed
a resistance to it,
so the poison is going
to kill you quickly.
It'll soon be over.
As for me...
I must be going on ahead...
[BULAT]
I should have expected
as much from you.
We have defeated each other.
[Coughing]
Bro!
Let's go patch you up!
Tatsumi...
We're not done yet sunshine;
I'm afraid this fight
isn't over.
[Flute playing]
Oh...
[NYAU]
Did you really think the Killer
Blood Swords were all we had?
Hm. So sorry.
The real trump card is me.
Trump Card:
Invite the Demonic Human.
[Flute playing]
This weapon is called Scream.
And it can do much more than
just make people go to sleep.
Like one little trick is making
myself bigger and stronger,
so I can tear your ass
to pieces.
Oh, man.
He made himself double
in size automatically!
That is one hell of
a trump card!
Ah...
Well now, it's been
kind of a long time.
It feels pretty good
to be back in this body.
[TATSUMI]
This is bad...
He was already
too hard to beat.
What the hell am I
gonna do now?
[BULAT]
Tatsumi...
[TATSUMI]
Uh?
[BULAT]
Tatsumi, here.
I'm leaving this to you.
[TATSUMI]
Is that...?
[BULAT]
The key to Incursio.
The armor will always belong to
the one who possesses the key.
No, you can't do that!
You can't give me Incursio.
[Nyau laughing]
What good will it do you
if you can't put it on?
Not just anyone can
wear that armor.
The wrong person
will die instantly
if they even try using it.
You might as well
just give it up.
Wouldn't want you to die before
we get a chance to play.
So quit being a coward
and fight like normal?
Hm...
Huh?
Uhh...
Are you really gonna let your
opponent tell you what to do?
Don't be ridiculous!
Look. You've had a lot of
training and gained some
great experience.
That's everything you need
to equip Incursio!
Alright?!
I don't know.
[NYAU]
Hmm.
I want to avenge my friends
by ripping this guy to shreds.
He can't just up and die on me.
[NYAU]
You need an affinity for
an Imperial Arms.
Yours won't be enough,
it'll kill you instantly.
If you like the way
a weapon feels...
Or even if you simply
have a positive first
impression of it,
you can usually tell
if it's a match.
Hyaa!
Whoa, so cool!
I promise you can do this.
You can! I know you can!
Okay, Bro.
Heh.
There's no one in the world
I respect more than you.
So if you say I can do it
then there's no way in hell
I'll let you down!
Ahh, seriously.
So you're really
gonna put it on?
Guess I better hurry
if I wanna kill you myself.
Time to die!
Let go and scream, Tatsumi!
With all the fire in your soul!
[Huge scream]
Incursio!
[BULAT]
Amazing...
The armor's changing its shape
to fit Tatsumi's physique!
Where'd that thing come from?!
That armor... are all the
materials still alive?!
[BULAT]
Incursio was created from parts
of a living dragon‐type Danger
Beast known as "Tyrant."
Its vitality is immensely high.
It can also adapt its body
to survive in any type
of environment,
from burning deserts
to the frozen tundra!
Even after becoming
an Imperial Arms,
the dragon's flesh is
still alive to this day!
Such a... such a
terrifying weapon!
[BULAT]
Tatsumi, your emotions
are causing it to evolve.
Incursio's bonding with you!
[TATSUMI]
Esdeath's army commited
Murder‐after‐murder using
Night Raid's name!
Now it's time for you to pay!
Yeah? You must think you're
pretty special now, don't you?!
I can feel it...
this armor is making
my body grow stronger.
[Grunt]
I'm about to finish this!
Ahhh!
I dare you to try!
[Yelling]
[Screams]
Aaah!
[Yelling]
Ha, whaddya know?
If that's how strong you are
right here and now,
then there's not a
single doubt in my mind.
One of these days
you will surpass me.
Ugh... Uhh...
[BULAT]
Go as far as you can, Tatsumi.
I'll be watching over you.
[TATSUMI]
I won, Bro...
I won because of you.
I'm sorry for that little
part at the end...
when I made you punch
some sense into me.
I swear, I'll get strong.
I promise, I'll master Incursio
and make you proud.
[Tatsumi crying]
So, just for now...
Is it okay if I cry for you?
Okay, Bro...?
[Huge scream]
[Crying]
[Kurome singing]
La la la...
Hehe...
Human bodies,
they're so amusing. Hehe...
The only way to pluck out
the weeds of rebellion
is pull directly from the roots.
Sending supplies to a foreign
tribe is a serious crime.
We did what needed to be done.
Kurome, I have a
message for you!
You're needed in the
Imperial Capital.
Huh?
They only ask for me?
That's right. Apparently you've
been personally selected
to be part of
a new group of six.
Group of six.
I heard that they were
planning on forming a new unit.
[KUROME]
Hmmm...
The Capital, huh?
Maybe I'll get to see you
again after all...
Big Sister.
[Music playing]