(gentle wind blowing)
Wait...
[IEYASU] Sorry. It's time for
us to be moving on, Tatsumi.
The two of us will be
going this way.
And you should head back, okay?
But how could you say that?
We've always stuck
together right?
You've got yourself a new group
of friends to look out for you.
C'mon, Tatsumi, we can't keep
babying you forever!
[IEYASU] Take care, man.
[SAYO] If there is an afterlife,
I'm sure we'll meet again.
No! Wait up!
Don't go!
Please!
Don't leave me here alone!
(gasps)
(uh...)
(soft sigh)
What a terrible dream...
(soft snoring)
What's she doing here?
(sleepy mumbling)
[SHEELE] Today, you'll be
training under me, Tatsumi.
I look forward to
working with you.
[TATSUMI]
Guess now it's her turn.
Okay, then... (huh)
(mmm...)
[SHEELE] (sigh)
Good morning, friend.
(waaah!) Where are my glasses?!
Oh!
Let's try this again, shall we?
Are you sure it's okay to leave
Sheele in charge of him?
(mmm) Oh, they'll be all right.
I am positive Sheele will
take a liking to him.
So, what makes you say that?
Tatsumi's quite popular
with older women.
Yep! That's why I call dibs
on being his trainer next!
See? He's a natural talent.
Ah, dammit, that is
such bullcraaaap!
You may go so far as to say
he's a lady KILLER.
Y'get it right?
Because he's an assassin?
(uuuuhhhh...)
Oh well, maybe next time.
So then about lunch...
I was thinking that I might
make some mapo beef bowls.
Well, I'd prefer if you
decide between mapo tofu
and beef bowls‐ (urk!)
[WOMEN] Sounds good!
[AKAME] And I'll top it off with
a little fried chicken, okay?
Fried chicken, too?!
Don't you think that's
a little bit much‐
Sounds good!
[LUBBOCK] Come on...
(sigh) Where the heck
do they put it all?
(unh, ugh...)
Congratulations, you learned
how to swim in armor!
[TATSUMI] (heavy panting)
[TATSUMI] (ugh) So heavy...
Man, that was really hard!
[SHEELE] It's a requirement as
part of our "How to Train
Assassins" curriculum.
I don't really do
any chores or anything,
so I kinda specialize in
training new recruits like you.
So why don't you do any chores?
[SHEELE] I tried to cook...
(whoosh!)
...but I burned the meat,
which made Akame a little upset.
Not the meat...
[SHEELE]
And I caused trouble for Bulat
when I tried to clean...
(laugh) Just let me do it.
[SHEELE] And Leone laughed at me
when I went shopping and
bought sugar instead of salt.
[LEONE] (boisterous laughter)
Why'd you buy so MUCH?
We tried laundry...
but I sorta ended up
washing Mine along with
all of the dirty clothes.
[MINE] (baaahhh!)
[TATSUMI]
Aww, don't feel too bad.
Yesss! Great job!
Oh, hey, I just realized.
Huh?
[TATSUMI]
When I first met the team,
you were the only one
who wasn't there.
(ack!)
Um... I'm sure there was a
reason, but I don't remember.
I'm such an airhead.
That's for sure.
[SHEELE]
I really do apologize. Oh!
Aww, not again...
So, how did you get into
this line of work?
Hmm?
Well, it's kind of
a complicated story.
I grew up in one of the older
parts of the Imperial Capital.
I've never been able
to do anything right.
(breaking glass)
I couldn't take pride in
a single thing I did.
People would always make
mean comments about me...
(laughing)
Like... like, maybe I was
crazy or something.
But thankfully...
I had a friend who was...
very kind to me.
No matter what happened
or how badly I messed up,
she never once made fun of me.
The time I spent with her was
the only ray of happiness
in my entire life.
But it...
it didn't last for long.
(rain & thunder)
(knocking on door)
One day I was visiting her
house, like I always did...
when a man came to the door.
He was her ex‐boyfriend.
He was furious and yelling
and breaking things.
(crash)
Then he tried to strangle her.
I think he was drunk
or on something.
My first thought was,
"I need to save my friend!"
I was surprisingly calm.
I couldn't believe
how quickly he died.
My friend was so scared
she started shaking.
But my head
was completely clear.
When it was all said and done,
the events of that night
were written off as
self‐defense.
But I never heard from my friend
again after that.
(mmm)
And then...
A few days later, the man's
friends came to get revenge.
They told me they'd
killed my parents
and they were going
to kill me next.
Despite all the awful
things they said,
I was incredibly relaxed.
(attack scream)
(urk...)
I killed them.
All of them.
One‐by‐one.
[THUGS] (ah!)
(panicked cries)
(gargh)
(ungh!)
That was the moment
I realized what I must do.
I'm good at this. At killing.
Maybe because
I'm a little crazy.
If I kill bad people, I can
make the world a better place!
I was a solo assassin
in the capital
when the Revolutionary Army
scouted me out.
I guess everyone
has a rough past.
Something to carry with them.
Do you... think I can do this?
[SHEELE] You'll do just fine.
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
(giggles)
(small sigh)
[SHEELE] Well, unlike me,
you're a very talented cook!
THAT'S what you
thought I meant?
[BULAT]
You're doing great, Tatsumi!
Huh?
(confident laugh)
Y'know, maybe I'm
NOT up for this.
[NAJENDA] Tatsumi, it seems
you've made a full recovery.
We've acquired
Zanku's Imperial Arms.
I want you to try it on.
Wow, you sure?!
It's for me?!
That one's all yours, sugar.
Careful, these things are known
for putting a lot of pressure
on your mind and body.
[TATSUMI] This eyeball thing
may not look all that cool,
but its abilities are
actually pretty amazing!
It wasn't in my book anywhere,
so we still don't have
much information on it.
Zanku was reading
people's minds with it.
See if you can make it work.
You're thinking...
"I can't wait to
eat meat tonight!"
[AKAME] (gasps) That's amazing!
[LEONE] Nope. He hasn't even
activated the stupid thing yet.
Well, I sure don't want him
to read MY mind.
It's supposed to have five
sights so quit stalling
and try one out.
Jeez, take a chill pill.
Okay...
O, random ability that
I don't know about...
activate now!
Whadda'ya see?
(waaahhh!)
[MINE] Don't have a cow!
Whoever invented
Imperial Arms...
[MINE] What's your problem?
was an absolute genius!
(ungh)
[LUBBOCK]
Crap, it's rejecting him!
I'm taking it off.
Man, my head really hurts...
It's not a match.
Your affinity's a little off.
You probably just didn't
like the way it looked
with your sweater.
They say your first impression
of an Imperial Arm
shows how well
you bond with it.
[TATSUMI] (uh...)
[NAJENDA] Let's have
headquarters examine it.
I'm sure it'll be a great asset
once we know a little more.
[AKAME] Sometimes on our
missions, we come across targets
who have Imperial Arms,
just as Headhunter Zanku did.
Our superiors prefer we try to
steal ‐ or destroy ‐
as many of them
as we possibly can.
[TATSUMI] So with every
Imperial Arms we get,
we're helping to further
advance the revolution?
That's right.
Here's a book about Imperial
Arms I'd like you to read.
There's so many...
and they're all different!
It's really unbelievable.
[NAJENDA]
You should memorize the details
of every weapon in there.
[TATSUMI] Wow...
So which one is
the most powerful?
It depends heavily on the user.
That said,
if I had to make a choice...
One can manipulate ice.
Its owner is quite strong.
Fortunately for us, though,
she's not in the Capital
right now.
She's trying to subdue the
people in the north.
Why the people in the north?
[NAJENDA]
The prince of the northern tribe
is known as Numa Seika.
He's a legendary hero who fights
with a spear and has never lost.
Not only is he a master
strategist,
but his people trust him very
deeply,
which makes him a threat
to the Empire.
He took over the northern
fortress capital
and made it into a base
for his tremendous army.
Since then, his forces have
begun to invade more and
more aggressively,
so the Empire formed a special
unit to fight them off.
[LUBBOCK] I don't think we
need to worry about that.
[NAJENDA] (ungh)
It'll take a year to stop the
northern tribe's army,
even for her.
We can only hope.
(smirk) (confident laugh)
Well, I say bring it on!
Let's go and get as many of
these things as we can!
You're in an awfully good mood.
What's gotten into you?
There's still some Imperial Arms
out there that we don't
know about, right?
Well, that gives me a
really great idea.
I mean they can do all
these amazing things!
So what if... maybe...
What if there's even an
Imperial Arms that can bring
people back from the dead!
Y'know? Right?
If there is, I can bring
Sayo and Ieyasu back!
All we have to do
is keep looking!
[BULAT] Oh, honey.
[TATSUMI] (huh?)
[TATSUMI] What?
Not even an Imperial Arms can
bring the dead back to life,
Tatsumi.
We only get one shot at life.
No! No, you don't know
that for sure!
We just have to find
it out there!
Then what about
the first Emperor?
[TATSUMI] (uh)
If he could've done that,
he'd still be alive.
He probably saw it
was impossible
and that's why he made Imperial
Arms in the first place.
(aaahhh...)
Just forget it.
If you don't let go
of that weakness,
the enemy will surely see it.
And if that happens,
it'll get you killed.
(grrr...)
Tatsumi, shouldn't you be
going to bed soon?
[TATSUMI]
I was so happy when I thought
they might come back to life.
I knew it was crazy,
but I thought there might be
some small chance.
(sobbing)
I'm really not gonna get to
see them ever again, am I?
I thought I had accepted that...
(sobbing)
Tatsumi...
I promise not to tell
anybody else about this.
So go on and cry
as much as you need to.
(sniffling)
Is it okay...
for you to be this nice to me?
It's all right.
I don't see any problem with it.
Maybe.
[TATSUMI] (quiet laugh)
Yeah, you would say that.
Sheele...
[SHEELE] (huh)
Thank you...
I should be thanking you,
Tatsumi.
Because of you, I've found
another way to make
myself... useful.
(dog‐like panting)
[SOLDIER]
You conquered the northern tribe
incredibly quickly.
Most impressive,
General Esdeath!
[ESDEATH]
I can't believe you were the
best they had to offer.
[SEIKA] (dog‐like panting)
How very disappointing.
(smack!)
Will we ever find an enemy
out there who can
satisfy my appetite?
(smirk)
[TATSUMI] Look at this place.
There's a lot going on!
[LEONE]
Yep! It's a lively part of town.
When you're born poor,
you gotta keep yourself busy.
So how've you been, Leone?
I could use one of
your backrubs!
Hey, we should go and
get a drink sometime!
Leone! Will you come and
play with me later?
Man, you sure are popular
with these people.
That's because this is the part
of town where I grew up.
I know it sounds crazy
but I was famous around here
for my back massag‐ (huh?)
[ANGRY MAN]
Look, it's Leone!
(angry mob)
Oh, crap!
[TATSUMI] (wah?) Uh, hey, wait!
Come back here!
Where's my money?!
Where is it?!
So, what do you think about
my old neighborhood?
(angry mob)
I love it!
It's really freakin' great!
I hope I don't end up on one
of your friend's hit lists.
[SOLDIER] Reporting in!
It appears General Nakakido and
General Hemi have defected.
They've abandoned their posts
and joined the rebel troops!
But General Nakakido was
an expert at combat.
The number of rebel forces is
increasing at an alarming rate.
If we don't move,
they could destroy the empire.
We must not lose faith!
They're situated so far south
that we may contend with them
at our leisure.
If we want to completely clear
out the seeds of rebellion,
then we should begin by
rounding them all up!
Isn't that right, Minister?
(laughing)
Well said, Your Highness!
I see you're keeping
your composure.
Our current issue...
(gnawing & smacking)
...is the rogue group of
assassins, not the rebels!
They killed Captain Ogre and
my dear relative Yokal.
(splat) (gunshot)
They murdered Headhunter Zanku
and took his Imperial Arms!
(shwack)
Damn Night Raid is making
a mess of the capital!
I'm gaining weight from
all this undue stress!
(gnawing & smacking)
I'm calling back
General Esdeath.
(gasps)
Um, forgive me, Minister,
but General Budo is
already here.
[MINISTER] I'm sure the Great
General has better things to do
than hunt down
a gang of bandits.
Esdeath, huh?
Her accomplishments ARE
equal to that of Budo.
We can trust her.
[MINISTER]
She slaughtered 400,000
tribesmen by burying them alive.
I don't need her
to capture them.
I want her to track down
and kill as many of them
as possible!
[TATSUMI] (panting)
Whew, I think we lost 'em.
You okay, Sis‐ (huh?)
Wait...
Where's...
Leone?!
Oh no, I can't find her.
And I have no idea where I am!
(confused babbling)
[SERYU] What's this?
Looks like my Justice Sensor
has found something!
You there!
Huh?
You seem to need
assistance, citizen!
(boing ‐ boing)
(uh...) That uniform...
Proud member of the Imperial
Guard, Seryu, at your service!
She's a guard...
(sad) Woorf... Woorf...
Koro, you hungry, buddy?
We'll eat soon.
[KORO] Woof, woof?
Sorry... what IS that?
He's my Imperial Arms,
Hekatonkeiru!
Don't worry,
he only bites bad guys.
He was in that book.
Oh, that's right,
you needed help, didn't you?
[TATSUMI] No, no, I'm fine!
I just got a little
turned around.
I think I remember the name
of the place I was before.
I'll help you find it!
[KORO] (surprised) Woof!
I'm on patrol right now anyway!
Let's go.
I won't let you get lost.
[TATSUMI] (uh...)
(angry) Wooofff!
[SERYU] (huh?)
[KORO] (angry) Woorf! Woorf!
[TATSUMI] So uh...
do all the Imperial Guards have
a weird angry pet like this?
[SERYU] Of course not!
I'm the only guard
who has an Imperial Arms.
[KORO] (whimpering)
Koro... um...
Well, that's the name
I've given him anyway.
He won't cooperate with anyone
unless he can tell
they have an extremely high
affinity with him.
Supposedly, none of the
top‐ranked officers were
able to click with Koro.
So they started running tests
on low‐level grunts like me.
I was told that he responded
to my righteous heart
while I was getting examined.
And he's been my cute,
little companion ever since.
Right, Koro?
[KORO] (excited) Woorf! Woof!
Oookaaay...
[SERYU]
Okay, I'm pretty sure this is
the place you're looking for.
[TATSUMI] (relieved sigh)
Thank you so much.
I'm honored. And let me know
if you see anything evil.
You can depend on us
to rip it to pieces!
(nervous laugh) That makes me
feel safe, I guess.
[SERYU] Time to go, little
buddy! You still hungry?
Let's pick out a few death‐row
prisoners for you to snack on!
[KORO] (painful) Woorf! Woorf!
(big sigh)
A guard with an Imperial Arms?
This could get ugly.
I'd better tell the boss.
[SERYU] I know it's
important to help people,
but I must be vigilant,
and locate Night Raid!
I MUST... for Captain Ogre...
(yah!)
[OGRE] (laughing)
Those are some nice
punches there, Seryu!
You're getting stronger
every day, aren't cha?
I was lucky an
Imperial Arms chose me.
So now I will make myself
more powerful!
(hyah!)
My father told me something
before he died!
"Justice must never
submit to evil!"
[OGRE] Oh? Well if you're
that eager to improve,
I could give you a trump card.
How'd ya like that?
You'd really do that?!
[OGRE] I know a doctor
who's been looking
to perform a few experiments.
But I should probably warn you,
the procedure's gonna
hurt like hell.
No problem at all!
I'm willing to do anything I can
to help the fight against evil!
Those monsters murdered
Captain Ogre!
Night Raid...
you will pay with your lives!