[SHALLTEAR]
For being at a disadvantage,
you did very well
to get this far.
[AINS] Honest praise.
I'll accept it graciously.
Now then.
Do you have any last
words before I end you?
[AINS]
Let's see.
I suppose I could go
on and on about how
I'm defenseless without my MP.
Or I could commend
you for so expertly
backing me into a corner.
Instead, I think I'll
thank you for fighting me
with everything you had.
And ensuring my victory.
If you had fought
me any other way,
I would have never been able to
execute my plan so flawlessly.
[gasps]
[AINS] In Player Versus Player,
otherwise known as PVP,
the most crucial part
of combat is deceiving
your opponent with
false information.
For instance, you could
change your armor
so that holy attacks
aren't very effective.
But still act as though
they cause you damage.
Or hide the fact that
you're still weak to fire
by fighting through the pain
and keeping your composure.
I knew you could
use Life Essence
to check the state of my HP.
So I cast False Data, Life
before we started.
But you were entirely
focused on my MP.
The next time you engage in PVP,
you should constantly
check both.
Knowing everything about
your enemy is vital
if you want to
execute your strategy.
I learned a lot
about your abilities
while my friend, Peroroncino,
was creating you.
You were his pride and joy.
And ever since we came to this
world, I've made it a point
to memorize all the data
concerning Nazarick's NPCs.
Even so, after Pandora's
Actor, the one I know
the most about is probably you.
But you didn't know my skills.
You said so!
[AINS]
I was lying, of course.
I thought you'd use them more
boldly if I feigned ignorance.
If you had saved
Negative Impact Shield
until the very end, I doubt
I'd be standing here
talking about this.
[growling]
[yells]
[AINS]
"Perfect Warrior"!
[SHALLTEAR growls]
[gasps]
[AINS] Everything has
played out as I expected.
Now, we'll finish
this hand-to-hand.
[COCYTUS gasps]
Impossible!
I thought that armor
was lost forever!
It does look familiar.
[COCYTUS]
It should.
It belonged to Lord Touch Me.
But it can only be worn by a
world champion class warrior.
Lord Ains is a caster!
[DEMIURGE]
Perfect Warrior!
[COCYTUS, ALBEDO]
Huh?
The spell Lord Ains just used.
It allowed him to change
to the warrior class
and use their equipment
without penalty.
[COCYTUS]
Still.
The fact that he can don world
champion armor is astounding.
Oh! My beloved
is truly wonderful!
[screaming]
I know that sword!
Takemikazuchi... Hachishki?
[COCYTUS]
That belonged to the
Lord Warrior Takemikazuchi!
[gasps]
[AINS]
Didn't I tell you, Shalltear?
Ains Ooal Gown does
not know defeat.
[gasps]
[AINS] You aren't facing one
Supreme Being, but 41.
The might of all Ains Ooal Gown
stands before you now.
Sorry,
but you were destined to fail
before this battle even started.
Shalltear Bloodfallen.
There is a reason the
Supreme Beings of Nazarick
chose me as their leader.
And you will
learn it first-hand.
Prepare yourself.
It's time I show you
the true terrifying power
of the man you call master!
[AINS grunts]
[SHALLTEAR grunts]
[SHALLTEAR groans]
[AINS gasps]
You're wide open!
[SHALLTEAR gasps]
[AINS]
I'm sorry.
Did you think you had me?
Those are Lord Nishikienrai's.
But... How did...?
[AINS, SHALLTEAR grunting]
[AINS grunts]
They're infused with holy magic!
Get away!
[AINS grunts]
[SHALLTEAR grunts, yelps]
How dare you make me
sound so un-graceful!
[gasps] No way. Houyi's Bow!
[SHALLTEAR]
I-Impossible. I'll kill you!
That is Lord
Peroroncino's weapon!
How did you-- No.
Where have you been hiding it?
[AINS]
Weren't you paying attention?
I used a cash shop item!
Cash shop? Those wooden sticks?
[SHALLTEAR]
I'm out of MP, and that weapon
can only be blocked by magic.
Even my special
skills are used up.
I was so reckless.
I should have
saved some of them.
No, wait.
[AINS]
Now do you understand?
Everything happened exactly
as I intended it to.
[screams] I won't let you!
[SHALLTEAR yells]
[AINS]
That's good resolve, Shalltear!
This is where the climax begins!
[COCYTUS]
Lord Ains is victorious.
Excuse me? How can
you know that?
The way I see it, this fight
is easily far from being over.
[COCYTUS] Shalltear has
given up on defense
and put everything into offense.
It's a desperate tactic.
I would make the same choice
were I in her position.
Lord Ains is changing weapons
faster than she
can keep up with.
Since Shalltear can't predict
what kind of weapon
he'll use next, it's
impossible for her to know
how to defend against it.
One step in the
wrong direction could
put her directly in the
path of his next attack.
And the bow's range forces
her to fight closer.
Shalltear has no choice.
All she can do is dodge his
attacks and hope to survive.
He has her cornered.
Thank you. Now I
understand the situation.
Since Shalltear has completely
given up on defense,
Lord Ains decided
to deploy the axe.
[COCYTUS]
Blood Sucking Meat Devourer.
[DEMIURGE]
Thanks, Cocytus.
Anyway, the axe itself
is highly unbalanced.
It's size and weight
forces the wielder
to swing without accuracy.
But since Shalltear has gone
purely offensive, it's no issue.
[COCYTUS]
Everything in this battle
has gone according
to Lord Ains' plan.
His strategy is the
work of pure genius.
However, Shalltear
can recover HP
if she lands a hit
with her Pipette Lance.
But Lord Ains cannot
cast any magical spells
as long as he's a Warrior. Isn't
he at a severe disadvantage?
I doubt it will be a problem.
Huh?
The Supreme One assured me
that he would claim
victory today,
and I believe he will.
There is nothing
Ains Ooal Gown cannot do.
[AINS, SHALLTEAR grunting]
[SHALLTEAR]
This feeling...!
[SHALLTEAR yells]
[SHALLTEAR giggles]
What's wrong, Lord Ains?
Your HP is dropping
faster than mine.
You'll run out first,
at this rate.
[AINS]
You really think so?
Huh?
[beeping]
[BUKUBUKU CHAGAMA]
Hey, Big Brother Momonga!
The timer you set is up!
That's Lady Bukubuku Chagama.
[AINS] I'm curious. What do you
think the timer was for?
[AINS] If everything up to
this point has transpired
according to my design,
then the timer running out
can only mean one thing
for the two of us.
[AINS]
This is the end of our fight.
We've reached the
Showdown. I've won.
That so? My HP says otherwise.
[AINS] A super tier magic
attack won't be able
to finish you when your
health is still full.
Which means all I had
to do was lower your HP
to the point that
it could. And I have.
[gasps]
[SHALLTEAR grunting]
[AINS]
I may be weak when it comes to
direct physical combat,
but my magic defense more
than makes up for it.
Here I come, Shalltear!
[SHALLTEAR yelps]
[AINS]
"Super Tier Magic..."
Are you kidding me?
I could re-fill my HP
a dozen times over
before you even finish
casting this spell!
[gasps]
[AINS]
Hm.
Is that...? It, can't be!
Another cash shop item?
[yells]
[AINS]
"Fallen Down"!
[SHALLTEAR] Hail Lord
Ains Ooal Gown. My master.
Truly, the Supreme One
is the strongest
in all of Nazarick.
Goodbye, Aura.
[AURA]
So stupid.
What kind of vampire let's
herself get mind controlled?
Uh, did you say something, sis?
[AURA]
It's nothin'.
What about the fight?
It's obvious Lord Ains won.
Come on, we're headin' back.
Uh, right.
[AINS] All that's left is to
begin Shalltear's resurrection.
Albedo, I need you
to watch her name
while I perform the ritual.
If she is still
under mind control
once she is revived, I may
have to do the unspeakable.
Don't worry about it.
If that does come to pass,
we will be the ones
to take care of her.
[AINS]
Demiurge...
Please, lord.
It was hard enough to
watch our Supreme Ruler
face such danger without his
Guardians supporting him.
I could not bear to see
you do it a second time.
[AINS]
I hear you, but--
If Shalltear continues to
revolt against Nazarick,
then the Guardians of Nazarick
should deal with her.
Please step down, my lord.
[AINS sighs]
I understand.
Then, if that happens,
I will let you deal with it,
my Guardians.
We won't fail you.
All we ask is that
you stay by our side.
If you leave us, who will
we pledge our fidelity to?
Without a Supreme Being to rule,
the Guardians would cease
to have a purpose.
Sorry.
We know our creators
didn't reject us.
Still, it is far too lonely
when no one is here.
[AINS]
You're right.
It is lonely when
everyone else is gone.
[AINS] Continue to
protect me, my Guardians!
Now, let us begin!
[GUARDIANS]
Lord!
[MOMONGA] It will cost 500
million gold to revive her.
[AINS]
Shalltear. "Resurrect"!
Albedo?
Be at ease, my lord.
It would seem she is free
of the mind control.
[AINS]
Wonderful.
Shalltear.
Is that you, lord?
[AINS] Thank goodness.
I'm sorry, Shalltear.
This was all because
of my mistake.
No. Please, lord.
I'm not sure what's
going on here, but...
...being in your arms couldn't
possibly be a mistake.
[AINS]
Uh-- Ah--
So this is where
my first time will be.
Excuse her, lord.
I believe Shalltear
is still out of it.
Huh?!
[AINS]
You must be tired.
Huh? Oh.
[AINS]
We'll go over the details later.
There's one thing
I'd like to know.
How did I get back to Nazarick
when I was just hunting
humans in the woods?
Oh and, why am I
naked on the floor?
And why is everyone
acting so strange?
I hope I didn't cause some
kind of trouble for you
or Nazarick, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
You don't remember?
Uh. No.
[AINS]
I'm sorry, Shalltear.
Then, please tell me
what you remember last.
[SHALLTEAR] Well. Other
than hunting the humans,
I remember giving you my regards
before leaving the great
Tomb to join Sebas.
After that, we rode a
carriage into a large town.
[MOMONGA] So the one who used
the world class item on her
remains a mystery. Of course.
[AINS]
Do you feel strange in any way?
I feel like I usually do.
[AINS]
I see.
Ah! Oh, no!
[AINS, ALBEDO gasp]
It's gone! My chest
is a wash-board!
[ALL groan]
[ALBEDO]
You lamprey!
Shalltear, do you have any
idea how much suffering
you put the rest of us through?
So, you've
conveniently forgotten.
But your peers still
remember your blunder!
What?
[AURA]
What an idiot.
You did something
unforgiveable to Lord Ains!
Aren't you ashamed of it?
Huh?
I'm beginning to
question whether
you understand the meaning of
your existence as a Guardian.
[COCYTUS]
Lord Ains' heart went through
such unbearable pain.
[MARE]
Yeah! I'm angry with you, too!
[ALBEDO] You always drown
in your own desires
without thinking
of the consequences.
[AINS chuckles]
[AINS grunts]
[AINS sighs]
[AINS]
Hm?
We await your orders.
[GUARDIANS chuckle]
[AINS]
Albedo.
As leader of the Guardians,
I recommend scolding
her mercilessly.
I second that.
Don't go easy on this
bone-head, Lord Ains.
[COCYTUS]
Agreed.
Harsh words are the least
she deserves at this point.
Shalltear,
accept your punishment with
humility and grace, okay?
Well, you don't have to be
too hard on her, lord.
Uh. If you don't mind.
[AINS laughs]
[AINS]
I deserve the scolding.
Despite all the information
we had gathered,
I never thought something like
this would be a possibility.
The mistake was mine and
mine alone, understand?
Shalltear, you are not
guilty of anything.
I want you to
remember that, always.
Ah! Thank you
very much, Lord Ains.
[AINS] Demiurge, you will
explain everything to her
once she's had the
chance to rest.
Lord. By the way.
Sebas failed to return
to Nazarick as ordered.
[AINS]
He is bait.
[gasps]
[AINS] We still don't know who
targeted Shalltear, or why.
But, since Sebas was with her,
there is a strong possibility
that he will be next.
Albedo.
I want you to gather a
team trained in stealth
and have them scout
the area near Sebas.
[ALBEDO]
Lord.
[AINS]
He may be bait.
But I have no intention
of letting our enemy bite.
If they make even the
slightest move on Sebas,
we will end them.
[MOMONGA] Someday, we will
meet the one who used
the world class item
on Shalltear.
And when we do, I will pay
back this debt 1,000 fold.
Uh. Question, master.
[AINS]
What is it, Mare?
You left a big scar
on the forest.
Would you like me to
repair the damage for you?
[AINS]
There's no need for that.
Huh?
[AINS]
Didn't you know?
If you destroy a
magic sealing crystal,
the unleashed power
will go wild.
It's even capable of destroying
a large area, apparently.
What? No, I had
never heard that.
[AINS]
Because I just made it up.
But the people of E-Rantel
will accept it as truth.
And since sealing crystals
are rare in this world,
I doubt anyone will
waste one to test it.
Also. I made a major
miscalculation before.
It is now plainly obvious
that someone out there
has the strength
to harm Nazarick.
And if there's one,
there could be others.
I want to take immediate steps
to strengthen Nazarick.
I was thinking of using
my necromancy skills
to make an army of undead.
But we would need
bodies to turn.
I've actually been
thinking about that, lord.
[AINS]
Hm?
It's true that undead soldiers
could protect us
from most intruders.
But they are relatively
powerless overall.
Case in point, one human corpse
can only become an undead
of level 40 or below.
[AINS]
You make a good point.
There's a village of
lizard men in the area.
Aura found them while scouting.
I wonder what kind of undead
their corpses would make.
[MALE PRIEST 13A] You're saying
the Black Scripture--
the strongest sect of the
entire Slane Theocracy--
were defeated by
one measly vampire?
Yes, your holiness.
Lady Kaire tried to stop it,
using the Downfall of
Castle and Country.
But, she was injured
before the mind control
could fully take hold. We
retreated shortly after that.
[PRIEST 13B] How do you propose
we deal with this situation?
[PRIEST 13C] We don't know
the whereabouts of Nigun
from the Sunlit Scripture.
And the Windflower Scripture
is currently pursuing
the traitor that stole
the Crown of Wisdom
from the shaman princess.
With our forces spread so thin,
the only thing we can
do is keep the area
under basic surveillance.
[PRIEST 13A] And, if there
is someone with the power
to defeat that monster,
we should be wary
and keep our distance for now.
Understood, your grace.
[NPHIREA]
Is that everything?
Yep. We're locked up
and ready to go.
Well, Miss Nabe.
We're in your hands now.
I will escort you to Carne.
Once we're there, my comrade
will take care of you.
Please, follow
her orders exactly.
Right. Let's get going.
[NPHIREA, LIZZY]
Huh?
[LIZZY]
When did they put a wall there?
[NPHIREA]
It's even bigger than last time.
Nphirea!
Enri!
[LUPISREGINA giggles]
Hey, there! Nice to meet you.
Lord Ains has ordered
me to take care of you.
I'm Lupisregina,
but call me Beta.
--[thunder rumbling]
--[gasps]
[GAZEF gasps]
I know you.
Unglaus. Brain Unglaus?
Gazef. I'll be damned.
[ADVENTURER 13A] That's the
third adamantite class
adventurer in all Re-Estize.
[ADVENTURER 5C]
So that's him.
Momon, the Raven Black Hero.
And Princess Nabe's with him.
Hey.
I heard they were the ones
who destroyed that chunk
of forest while
they were fighting.
You believe that?
They might be strong,
but they're still human.
Only a handful of people
could pull that off, though.
That's why adamantite is the
highest class you can get.
I wouldn't be surprised
if he ends up being
the most powerful
adamantite of all time.
[AINS] We've already
finished the last job.
We'd like another one, please.
Something more challenging.
I'm so sorry. I don't have any.
None of the current postings
are worth an adventurer
of your caliber, Mr. Momon.
--[AINS] I see.
--[beeping]
[AINS] Actually, you know
what? That's perfect.
[QUEST-GIVER 5A]
Huh?
[AINS] I remembered
something important.
I'll be in my room.
If anything comes up,
will you let me know?
Yes. The Inn of
Shining Gold, right?
[AINS] Order Gargantua to
activate. Call Victim as well.
Have the Guardians ready to move
by the time Cocytus returns.
This time, we're all
going in together.