[SHALLTEAR] My, my. It appears
I'm the first to arrive.
[MOMONGA]
Shalltear. A true vampire.
She guards the first,
second, and third floors
of the Great Tomb of Nazarick.
Oh, wow! Lord Momonga!
The one man I could
never rule above!
My eternal beloved!
[MOMONGA]
Wha-- Hey!
Stop, Shalltear.
You're starting
to slobber on him.
[SHALLTEAR] Hello, half-pint.
I didn't realize you were here.
[grunts]
[SHALLTEAR] Having such
a foolish older sister
must be difficult, Mare.
However do you manage it?
Miss Fake Tits.
What?!
Just as I thought!
That's why you went through
the trouble of using a gate.
You were in a hurry,
but since you overstuffed
your top so much, you worried
they would shift
if you ran here.
Ah! Watch it, elf!
You've got nothing
but a boy-chest!
True, but I'm only 76 years old.
I can still develop.
Whereas, you're stuck
in an undead body.
Maybe you should learn
to accept those bug bites.
How dare you!
I'll make sure you regret that!
[MOMONGA]
Talk about nostalgic.
Shalltear's creator,
Peroroncino,
and his older sister,
Bukubuku Chagama,
who created Aura and Mare,
used to have fights
like this all the time.
[COCYTUS]
What a ruckus.
[AINS]
Hm?
[COCYTUS] Stop acting like
children in front of the master.
[MOMONGA] Cocytus. He's the
guardian of the fifth floor,
and a virtual personification
of the word "Warrior."
I'll stop once this elf
bitch pays for her lies!
[AURA]
Try it, vamp!
[AINS]
That's enough!
Shalltear. Aura.
We don't have time
to be playing around.
[AURA, SHALLTEAR]
Forgive me, my lord.
[AINS]
I'm glad you're here, Cocytus.
[COCYTUS] I will always
come when you call.
[AINS]
Mm. Good work.
[DEMIURGE]
Sorry, everyone.
I hope you weren't
waiting too long.
[MOMONGA] Demiurge. He's an
insanely powerful demon,
and guardian of the
Tomb's seventh floor.
If Nazarick is ever in
crisis, he is set to lead
the other NPCs in its defense.
My lord. We, the Guardians,
pledge our fidelity.
[MOMONGA] The world of the
massively popular DMMO-RPG,
Yggdrasil, drastically changed
after its last day of service.
Though magic can still be used,
various rules have
changed and the NPCs
have begun to move
of their own volition.
[AINS]
Raise your heads.
[MOMONGA]
Jeez, could I look any more
depressed and hopeless?
[AINS] I am very pleased
that all of you have come.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Your thanks are wasted on us.
We have pledged ourselves to
you, and live to obey, lord.
I fear that our
abilities may not
meet your expectations.
Despite this, we will
strive to meet them,
in honor of the
lost Supreme Beings,
our blesséd creators,
this, we vow!
[GUARDIANS]
This, we vow!
[AINS]
Most excellent, my Guardians!
I have no doubt that
all of you will fulfill
your duties without fail!
[AINS]
Now, then.
[GUARDIANS gasp]
[AINS] The situation outside
the Great Tomb of Nazarick is,
at present, entirely
unknown to us.
With this in mind,
I've had Sebas survey
the surrounding area.
[AINS]
Grasslands?
[SEBAS]
Yes, lord.
I'm afraid the swamps
that once surrounded
the Great Tomb of Nazarick
are nowhere to be seen.
Furthermore, I could not
confirm a single building,
human, or monster within
one kilometer of here.
It would seem we are
completely isolated.
[AINS] Very good, Sebas.
You've served me well.
As I suspected, it appears
that Nazarick has been
transported to an
unknown land by equally
mysterious means.
Floor Guardian leader Albedo,
and defensive leader Demiurge.
I have a task for you.
[DEMIURGE, ALBEDO]
Lord.
[AINS] Fortify our defenses
and work on a way
to strengthen our
information gathering.
The rest of you,
follow their lead.
[AURA, MARE, COCYTUS, SHALLTEAR]
Lord!
[AINS]
Mare, is there a way to conceal
the Great Tomb of Nazarick?
Yes, though, it
will be difficult
if all we use is magic.
But, if we covered the walls
with dirt and vegetation.
I think it would help to
camouflage us from intruders--
[ALBEDO] You want to smear
the glorious Nazarick
walls with dirt?
[AINS] Albedo! Don't
make needless remarks.
Yes. Forgive me, lord.
I was careless.
[AINS] Are you confident the
dirt will be sufficient, Mare?
Y-Yes. I am.
As long as you allow it,
of course. Except...
[AINS] Right. One random
mound would look unnatural.
Sebas, are there any
hills around the Tomb
we could blend in with?
No. The area is barren.
Nothing but flatlands as
far as the eye can see.
[AINS] Fortunately, the land can
be molded to suit our needs.
Would making dummy
hills suffice?
Yes, I do believe
we would blend in
with such a surrounding.
[AINS] Excellent, then
that is what we shall do.
Afterwards, we will use
illusion magic to hide
the open areas
we cannot cover.
[MARE] O-Of course, lord.
It will be done.
[AINS] Lastly, there is
a question I would have
each of you answer.
First, Shalltear.
In your own words, tell me what
kind of person I am to you.
Beauty incarnate.
There is nothing,
living or undead,
that could ever compare
with your radiant glow.
[AINS]
Cocytus.
[COCYTUS] A man whose
strength is unrivaled
by any guardian.
You are truly worthy of ruling
the Great Tomb of Nazarick,
always and absolutely.
[AINS]
Aura.
Compassionate.
And you're always three
steps ahead of the game.
[AINS]
Mare.
You're a leader who's
kind, as well as merciful.
[AINS]
Demiurge.
A man who makes wise
decisions then acts
upon them efficiently and
without any form of hesitation.
Also, your enigmatic nature
makes it nigh impossible
to predict you.
[AINS]
Sebas.
You are the head of all
the Supreme Beings,
and, even though the other
creators had left us behind,
you mercifully stayed in
Nazarick until the very end.
[AINS]
And lastly, Albedo.
You are the
highest-ranking member
of the Supreme Beings.
Our ultimate master,
and the ruler of Nazarick.
As well as the man to
whom my heart belongs.
[AINS]
U-Uh, y-yes, I see.
I have heard your thoughts,
and given you your orders.
Go work faithfully in my name.
[GUARDIANS]
Lord!
[MOMONGA sighs]
I'm beat.
Why the hell do they
have such glorious
views of me?
They're so... serious!
I thought I was going to
faint, that was so scary.
Seriously!
I was sure the pressure
would crush us!
[COCYTUS] To think he
would be this amazing.
When he shows his true
power and authority,
he's even more glorious
than I imagined.
[DEMIURGE]
Indeed.
[COCYTUS] He seemed pleased
with our vow of fidelity.
I hope that is the case.
He acted completely
different when he was alone
with Mare and me.
In fact, he was
super kind and gentle.
[ALBEDO gasps]
He even gave us
something to drink
because he thought
we looked thirsty.
That just proves
he's a true ruler,
through and through.
His power and mercy
make him amazing!
It's just as you say, Mare!
He was incredible, wasn't he?
He sensed our feelings and
acted on them accordingly.
Just as an absolute
ruler should!
Of the 41 Supreme Beings,
he stands at the top!
And when all of the others
had left us behind,
he mercifully stayed with us.
[SEBAS] If there's nothing more,
I'll return to my duties.
I do not know
where Lord Momonga
has gone within the Tomb.
But, wherever he is,
I should stay by his side.
Very well.
If anything happens, please
inform me immediately, Sebas.
Especially if Lord Momonga
calls for me personally.
I will rush to his side!
No matter what
I have to sacrifice!
But, if Lord Momonga
wants me to join him
in his bedchamber, then
I will need time to prepare.
I would need to bathe first.
Of course, if he wants me
to go without bathing,
--then I'd be happy--
--You've made yourself clear.
Now, if you will all excuse
me, I must take my leave.
[SHALLTEAR whimpering]
Is there something
wrong, Shalltear?
[COCYTUS]
Are you hurt? Ill?
No, I'm fantastic.
I just got a little
over-stimulated, is all.
His power was so
intense, my underwear
went through a small crisis.
[GUARDIANS groan]
[ALBEDO]
Disgusting bitch!
[SHALLTEAR]
Ugh. What?
Don't pretend you
aren't thrilled
over the gift he just gave us.
He shared so much of his power.
If something that
incredible doesn't
make you wet, you must be
rancid beneath that skirt!
[ALBEDO]
You filthy parasite!
The Supreme Beings
made me what I am.
I take pride in it,
and a big-mouthed,
idiotic gorilla like you
won't change that.
Keep flapping those
fangs, Lamprey.
See where it gets you!
Right... Aura.
I'll let you deal
with the women issues.
Whoa, not so fast!
You can't dump this on me!
[DEMIURGE] If it starts to
get bloody, I'll intervene.
Um...
[COCYTUS]
Goodness.
Is this really something
worth fighting over?
You, too, Cocytus?
[ALBEDO, SHALLTEAR growling]
[DEMIURGE] Their vitriol aside,
I'd be quite interested
to see the result
of such a union.
What?
It would be a great
addition to our forces
and it would pave the way
for Nazarick's future.
I'm not sure I follow you.
[sighs] Every great ruler
needs an heir, don't they?
Uh?
Lord Momonga stayed
behind until the end.
However, one day, he may
leave to join the other
Supreme Beings,
wherever they went.
Therefore, it would be
nice if he left an heir
we could pledge our
loyalty to. Agreed?
[MARE]
Um.
So, you're saying that one
of them should give birth
to Lord Momonga's heir?
[COCYTUS]
Blasphemy!
If we do our jobs,
that won't be needed.
Yes, of course.
But, instead of just
serving one lord,
we could pledge
ourselves to his line.
[COCYTUS]
Oh? That would be kind of nice.
No, it would be wonderful!
I can see it so clearly now!
I would be Uncle Cocytus!
By the way, Mare?
Is there a particular reason
you're wearing female garments?
[MARE] Actually, this is
something that Bukubuku Chagama
chose for me.
She said I was
a "cross dresser,"
or something like that.
Maybe wearing these
clothes makes it easier
for me to cast my magic spells?
[DEMIURGE]
Hm. Interesting.
Perhaps it would be fruitful
to try having the males
dress in female garments
at some point. Later.
Cocytus, come back
to reality, please.
[COCYTUS]
What a magnificent scene.
That is truly a
future to wish for.
[DEMIURGE]
I'm happy you're happy.
Aura! Have Albedo and Shalltear
finished their little spat?
Yeah, the catfight is over,
but now they're arguing.
We are deciding who the
master's head wife will be.
Obviously, the ruler of Nazarick
will have multiple wives.
It would be strange for
someone of Lord Momonga's
position and power
not to have a harem.
But only one of us can
be his official wife.
Yes, that's fascinating,
but, don't you think
we should focus on the task
the master set for us?
Yes, of course. Back to work.
But, Shalltear, we will
discuss this later, at length.
Looking forward to it.
Now, then. It's time
to begin planning.
[MOMONGA] I only took on
the class of magician, but,
since I'm level 100,
I should have enough
strength to swing a sword.
Let's see...
[gasps]
[MOMONGA] Looks like I still
can't wield or equip items
that aren't specific
to my in-game class.
It's been three days
since I came to this world,
and I haven't once felt
uneasy about my undead form.
Maybe my mentality changed
along with my body?
I know that if I get
emotionally unstable,
some outside force
makes me calm down.
That bears investigation.
I haven't felt the
need to eat or sleep
since I got here. Also,
I didn't act on my libido.
I guess that's another sword
I won't be wielding.
Shall I get that?
[AINS]
Yes. "Create Greater Item"!
[AINS grunts]
[MOMONGA]
It really is like Yggdrasil.
If a magic item allows it, I can
bypass my class restrictions.
[AINS]
Narberal.
I'm going to go outside
the Tomb for a bit.
The guards shall accompany you.
Just say the word.
[AINS]
No need. I will go alone.
Please wait, lord!
If you leave without an escort,
we would be unable
to protect you.
It is our sworn duty to act
as your shields, and perish.
[AINS]
I won't allow it.
There is something I
want to do discreetly.
My decision is made.
As you wish, my lord.
[AINS]
This is so tiring.
I won't be able to use
magic in this armor,
but I can make do with my items.
[MOMONGA gasps]
[MOMONGA]
Jealousy, Avarice, and Wrath?
Why are the three demon
generals under Demiurge
on the first floor?
[gasps]
[MOMONGA]
Demiurge.
[DEMIURGE]
It's you, my lord.
But, why are you traveling
without an armed escort?
And wearing such armor?
[MOMONGA]
Crap! How'd he know? Calm down.
Only someone wearing
a guild ring
can freely teleport
around Nazarick.
Of course he knew.
[AINS] Well, there is
a reason for all of this.
So that's how it is.
[MOMONGA]
Huh?
As expected of a great ruler,
your attention to
detail is impeccable.
[MOMONGA]
Wait. What?
I just wanted to go outside
for some fresh air!
However...
I can't let you to leave
here without an escort.
If something happened,
I couldn't forgive myself.
[AINS] Hm. Then, I will
allow you and you alone
to accompany me.
Thank you for indulging
my selfishness, lord.
I will not fail you.
[MOMONGA gasps]
[MOMONGA]
Amazing.
I've never seen a night
as clear as this before.
The artificial sky Blue
Planet made on floor six
was impressive, but it didn't
hold a candle to this.
[AINS]
"Fly"!
[DEMIURGE growling]
[MOMONGA] I can see everything
with just the moon's light.
I wish Blue Planet were
here to see this world's
unbelievable beauty.
[AINS] The stars in the
sky glitter like jewels
in a treasure box.
[DEMIURGE] I believe this
world exists so that you may
adorn yourself with
its infinite riches,
and we Guardians exist
to help you do so.
[AINS] Hm. You could
be right about that.
Perhaps I was sent to this
land to obtain those jewels
for myself, along
with every treasure
that shines beneath them.
But, to hoard such
things would be
the height of selfishness.
Instead, I could use them
to adorn the Great Tomb,
it's residents, and my
friends of Ains Ooal Gown.
If you wish it, we will
use all the power
of Nazarick to obtain
it for you, my lord.
[AINS laughs] We don't even know
what exists in this world.
It's a little early for a quest.
Then again, it makes me think.
The most enjoyable thing now
might be taking over the world.
[DEMIURGE gasps]
[MOMONGA]
Who am I kidding?
There's no way
we'd pull that off.
I wonder, though.
Am I really the only player
who came to this
world from Yggdrasil?
My message skill
didn't reach anyone,
but it might be because
they're too far away
or the effect of the
magic has changed.
[MOMONGA] If that's the case,
maybe I should spread
the name of Ains Ooal Gown
throughout this world.
[AINS]
Hm.
[MOMONGA]
That's Earth Surge.
He's using a skill to
increase his magic range,
and one of his class skills
to amplify the effect.
Well done, Mare.
[DEMIURGE]
Lord Momonga.
May I ask what you plan to do?
[AINS] I want to thank
Mare for his hard work.
What do you think I should
give him as a reward?
[DEMIURGE]
I am sure that he would be happy
just to have you
speak to him, my lord.
[AINS]
Mm...
Oh! Lord Momonga!
[MARE]
Why are you here?
Oh no, did I make
a mistake already?
[AINS]
Not at all, Mare.
The work you're doing is
of the utmost importance.
It will protect Nazarick
from intruders, and more.
[MARE]
R-Right.
[AINS] I wanted you to know
just how satisfied I am.
Your performance thus far
has been exemplary.
Um. Thanks, Lord Momonga.
[AINS]
I would like you to have this.
[MARE]
That's a Ring of Ains Ooal Gown!
But, only Supreme
Beings are allowed
to wear an item like this!
I can't possibly accept.
[AINS]
There's no need to panic, Mare.
Huh?
[AINS] Moving between Nazarick's
floors can be difficult.
This will allow you
to do so unimpeded
and easily complete your work.
Now, take this ring
and serve Nazarick well.
[gasps]
[gasps] Thank you so
very much, Lord Momonga!
I'll be sure to work
extra, extra hard for you
and the honor of
Nazarick, I swear it!
I'll be worthy of this gift!
[AINS]
I'm depending on you, Mare.
Yes! By the way, my
lord, I was wondering.
Why are you dressed like that?
[AINS]
U-Uh, um... Well... that's--
[ALBEDO]
It's simple, Mare.
[DEMIURGE]
Albedo.
It's for our sake.
He didn't want to bother any
of us while we were working.
It's like a disguise.
If we knew that he
was here watching us,
we would stop working
to praise him.
If that happened, then
nothing would get done.
Isn't that right, Lord Momonga?
[AINS]
As expected of Albedo!
You knew exactly
what I was thinking.
I'm leader of the floor
Guardians, my lord.
But, even without that title.,
I'm certain that I would sense
your thoughts and feelings,
as if they were my own.
[MARE]
Is that so?
[ALBEDO yells]
[AINS gasps]
Is there something
wrong, master?
[AINS]
U-Uh, no. Nothing at all.
Right, then. Mare.
Sorry for interrupting you.
You may return
to your work, now.
Oh, sure!
I'll get right on it, lord.
Please, excuse me.
[AINS]
Albedo.
I should give one
to you, as well.
"Give me one"? Of what, lord?
[AINS] This will make your
work as administrator
of the Guardians a little
easier. Use it wisely.
[ALBEDO]
Thank you very much.
[AINS gasps]
[gasping]
[AINS]
W-Work diligently.
Demiurge, I will prepare
one for you another time.
I understand, lord.
I only hope that, one day,
I can prove myself
worthy of such a treasure.
[AINS] I have done
what I planned to do.
I will return below before
I cause any more distractions.
Oh, yes!
We will attack the next
village tomorrow morning.
And guide the beasts
to their cages.
[AINS] After using a magic item
to survey the surrounding area,
I discover a human settlement.
A small village is dyed
red with blood and flames,
as a group of knights
brutally attacks it.
However, even as I watch the
massacre unfold before me,
I feel nothing at the loss
of all the innocent lives.
Perhaps... I've lost my humanity
along with my human form.
Chapter three: "Battle
of Carne Village."