[AINS]
Aura. Mare.
This is where we part ways.
Scout the area for enemies
as soon as we do. Understood?
[AURA, MARE]
Lord.
[AINS] But, if you find
yourself outnumbered by even
the smallest degree,
retreat to Nazarick at once.
Understood, Lord Ains.
We will do as you command.
[AINS] Excellent.
Make sure that you do.
Remember, your retreat
is an important part
of my overall plan. Also,
the Depiction of Nature
and Society and Avarice
and Selfless are world class
items, treasured by Nazarick.
They must never
be taken from us.
Depending on the situation,
they are more important
than your lives.
[BOTH]
Yes, lord!
[MOMONGA]
Strange.
I used magic to detect
the owner of the world item
that's controlling Shalltear,
but they aren't nearby.
Did they really just
leave her out here alone?
It doesn't make sense.
[DEMIURGE]
I've returned.
Now then. Care to
tell me what's going on?
You already know
the answer to that.
Everything Lord Ains told me
was conveyed over "Message."
I was referring to why you
let him go without support.
It was the master's call.
I simply obeyed it.
As I hope you intend to.
Why did you not protest?
We could have sent in minions
in case this is a trap.
If all the Guardians
fought together,
there isn't a force
that could overtake us.
I couldn't begin
to guess the reason
behind his decision.
But it is obvious that
Lord Ains was lying to us.
Don't pretend that
you didn't notice it!
Yes. It is as you say.
Then why did you allow him
to leave without support?!
When Lord Ains planned
to go to E-Rantel
without a Guardian escort,
you strongly objected to it,
so why would you possibly
be okay with him
doing the same thing now?
Because he was quite adamant
about defeating Shalltear
with his own two hands.
[gasps]
Ah...
[AINS]
If that's what you need,
then I promise you,
I will come back alive.
But first, I have
to defeat Shalltear.
His pure determination
was intense.
And, as a woman, seeing
my love so resolute,
I simply couldn't
bring myself to oppose
my dear Lord Ains'
wishes any further.
It may have been
irreverent of me,
but I've decided
I don't really care.
Besides, Lord Ains promised
he would return to us. I know in
my heart he will do just that.
So you made your
decision on emotion
instead of logic. Did you
forget he is the last
of the Supreme Beings
that created us?
It is our duty to
keep him from danger.
Even if that danger comes
from his own actions.
He may scold, or even
kill us for it,
but we must do something!
And where do you
think you're going?
I'm sure it's obvious.
My subordinates and I will--
[DEMIURGE sighs]
I see.
Now I understand why you
ordered me to meet you here
the moment that I arrived.
This was your plan
from the beginning.
That's correct.
You're a fool!
What if Lord Ains perishes
as a result of this folly?
Are you prepared to face the
consequences of that outcome?
We pledged our loyalty to him.
Once he is gone, there will
be no one left to serve.
He will return to us.
I'm sure of it.
You can't possibly know that!
You should believe
in your master.
As a Guardian, is that not
also one of your duties?
[grunts]
All right.
But, if something were
to happen to Lord Ains,
I will demand that you step down
as leader of the Guardians!
[COCYTUS] You would have
her relinquish a position
the Supreme Beings
placed her in?
That is blasphemy, Demiurge,
of the highest caliber!
As you wish. Tell me, Cocytus.
What do you think are the odds
of Lord Ains being victorious?
[COCYTUS] Three to seven.
Three in Lord Ains' favor.
[gasps]
I see.
Then, let's watch
as the battle unfolds
and witness our glorious
master beat the odds.
[AINS]
Dammit!
[AINS] I wanted to spread
the name of Ains Ooal Gown
so that my comrades
might find me.
I planned to do
whatever was necessary.
Still, I made sure
to move in secret,
so that I could avoid
unnecessary fighting
along the way.
So, how?
How could something
like this happen?
I don't know who did this yet.
But, when I do,
I will destroy them.
I'll make sure
they deeply regret
standing in my way.
They've started a fight
with Ains Ooal Gown,
and that is the fastest
way to the grave.
[MOMONGA]
I'm so stupid.
I know there are better
ways of handling this.
Aura and Mare seemed
to be convinced,
but I'm pretty sure Albedo
saw through my lie.
As for you, don't you think this
is a huge gamble
as well, Shalltear?
I don't even know if the
resurrection mechanics
back in Yggdrasil
exist in this world.
But I'm about to start a battle
with our lives on the line.
Because...
I'll be the one
to kill her instead.
[MOMONGA] Because I couldn't
bear to watch any of you
try to kill each other.
[MOMONGA]
And...
[AINS]
I am the great Ains Ooal Gown.
This sacred name can never
be tarnished by defeat!
"Body of Effulgent Beryl"!
[AINS laughs]
As I suspected.
Unless I pull aggro
with an actual attack,
you won't go into
combat mode, will you?
Just like any MMO boss fight.
[AINS]
Sorry, Shalltear.
But I'm taking full
advantage of this.
You'll have to wait
a little longer.
"Fly." "Blessing of
Magic Caster."
"Infinity Wall."
"Magic Ward, Holy."
"Life Essence."
"Greater Full Potential."
"Freedom." "False Data, Life."
"See Through."
"Paranormal Intuition."
"Greater Resistance."
"Mantle of Chaos."
"Indomitability."
"Sensor Boost."
"Greater Luck." "Magic Boost."
"Draconic Power."
"Greater Hardening."
"Heavenly Aura."
"Absorption." "Penetrate Up."
"Greater Magic Shield."
"Mana Essence."
"Triple Maximize Magic,
Explode Mine."
"Triple Magic,
Greater Magic Seal."
"Triple Maximize Boosted
Magic, Magic Arrow"!
[AINS]
Let's begin.
[AURA]
What's that?
I... think it's maybe
super tier magic.
That's supposed to be even
stronger than tenth tier.
Isn't it a little
early for that?
It's more like a skill.
It doesn't use any MP.
[COCYTUS] It may be free
to cast, but, once it's used,
he won't be able
to cast it again.
A bold tactic, to say the least.
What is his plan?
Perhaps he wants to diminish
Shalltear's HP quickly,
so she won't have
time to counter him.
[AINS]
Still no enemies. Interesting.
They could be hiding
in wait for me.
But I can't waste this
opportunity to attack.
Goodness. I'm really
going in blind here.
[beeping]
[BUKUBUKU CHAGAMA]
I'll set that timer for you,
Big Brother Momonga!
[MOMONGA]
Bukubuku Chagama.
I wonder why I can't mute
the voice on this watch.
[MOMONGA]
I will borrow some strength.
From all of you.
[AINS]
Now then. Let's go.
Super Tier Magic! "Fallen Down"!
[laughing]
Be careful, Lord Ains!
I might think you're trying
to kill me! Nice try!
[AINS]
It wasn't much of a present,
but I hope you that
you enjoyed it.
Oh. I most certainly did!
What a treat this will be.
I get to enjoy killing a
powerful man like Lord Ains
with my own two hands.
How wonderful!
[AINS] Interesting. Why are
you still calling me that?
Oh, come on, isn't it obvious?
You are still one of the
Supreme Beings, Lord Ains.
Calling you anything
less than that would be
the height of arrogance.
[AINS]
Who is your master, Shalltear?
What kind of question
is that, lord?
[gasps] This doesn't make sense.
Why do I want to kill
my beloved master?
Because I was attacked?
Because I feel compelled to?
I have to use all of
my strength to counter
and destroy whoever
tries to bring me harm.
But why him?
I don't know what's going on.
But, now that I've been
attacked, I have no choice
but to tear you limb
from limb, master.
[AINS]
I see. Very well, then.
[MOMONGA]
I know what's going on here.
[SHALLTEAR]
You seem a tad underdressed
for the occasion, master.
Did you actually think
you'd be able to beat me
wearing nothing but dirty rags?
[AINS] Ha! Ains Ooal Gown
does not know defeat.
Before the day is done,
you will bow down
before me again, Shalltear.
[laughs] Oh, I'm just
aquiver with fear!
[AINS]
Watch your step.
[gasps]
[AINS]
You should be more careful.
I've cast the Triple Maximize
Magic, Exploding Mine
in the area surrounding me.
"Maximize Magic,
Gravity Maelstrom"!
[SHALLTEAR grunts]
"Wall of Stone"!
[AINS]
"Maximize Magic, Hold of Rib"!
[gasps]
[AINS] By the way,
I forgot to mention this.
I've littered the ground
with all kinds of traps.
Why don't you flap
those wings over to me?
Shame on you.
I will not be provoked
that easily, Lord Ains.
I'm sure you've made the air
around you equally as deadly.
[AINS]
Was it that obvious?
Of course. I'm no fool.
[MOMONGA]
She bought it.
That was the only
mine spell I cast.
I don't have enough
MP to waste on magic
that might not give results.
I have to play this smart.
I wonder how much I'll
be able to damage her
before I completely drain my MP.
[SHALLTEAR]
As expected of Lord Ains.
If I continue to rush in, it's
not going to get me anywhere.
However, as a magic caster,
his strength only exists
as long as he has MP left.
If I can force him to use
it all, he won't be able
to counter my constant
physical attacks.
He'll be finished.
This Pipette Lance
allows me to heal
myself whenever I land
a hit on an opponent.
And the amount of HP
I receive is equal
to the damage caused.
Because of that,
Lord Ains cannot
summon a creature to fight
on the front lines for him.
He knows that weak level
monsters will only
feed my Pipette Lance and
keep me alive indefinitely.
His spells are his only option.
Aw, my poor, beloved, Lord Ains.
He has to fight me all alone.
It must be so frustrating.
That said...
"Mana Essence."
He has a staggering
amount of MP.
How did he manage to
obtain this much power?
Fortunately, his
specialization in necromancy
won't give him the fighting
edge. I still have a chance.
It bothers me that
he's not wearing
his usual god level items.
But a staring match
will get us nowhere fast.
I should heal and prepare
for the long haul.
"Regenerate"!
[AINS]
I won't make it that easy!
"Maximize Magic,
Gravity Maelstrom"!
"Greater Teleportation"!
[SHALLTEAR gasps]
How did he stop me?
[AINS]
"Drifting Master Mine"!
Not good enough!
"Maximize Magic,
Astral Smite"!
[AINS] "Maximize Magic,
Thousand Bone Lance"!
[SHALLTEAR]
"Greater Teleportation"!
[AINS]
Get back here!
"Negative Impact Shield"!
[AINS]
What?
You look so surprised.
Did you not know that
I had a skill like this
in my arsenal, Lord Ains?
[AINS]
No. But it won't save you.
[laughs] I love watching
you try to play tough.
It's absolutely adorable.
[SHALLTEAR] Do you know
about my Purifying Lance,
or should I explain it, too?
[AINS]
It summons a holy object.
[AINS groans]
[SHALLTEAR laughs] For a weapon
meant to battle magic casters,
it doesn't disappoint, does it?
I don't think I've seen anything
work so well against you.
[AINS groans]
[AINS]
Don't underestimate me!
"Maximize Magic,
Reality Slash"!
[grunts]
[AINS] That wasn't
normal recovery magic.
What did you do?
What's the matter, Lord Ains?
It seems like you're
losing your composure.
Don't worry, I didn't cheat.
That was another one
of my special skills.
Lord Peroroncino saw fit to
grace me with many of them.
I dare say his foresight proves
that he was far superior to you
as a Supreme Being.
[AINS]
Is that how you truly feel?
Huh?
[AINS]
Let's do this, Shalltear.
It doesn't matter how many
special skills you have.
My magic will
always be stronger.
Well, if it's a
shoot-out you want,
I'd be happy to play along.
Don't cry when I win.
[SHALLTEAR] I can only
use these so many times.
[AINS]
"Maximize Magic, Reality Slash"!
"Purifying Lance"!
[SHALLTEAR, AINS groan]
Be careful, Lord Ains.
You're running low on MP.
[SHALLTEAR]
I may have used up my skills,
but I still have
plenty of MP left.
Let's see how you
handle my spellcraft!
"Maximize Magic,
Vermillion Nova!"
[AINS] "Triple Maximize Magic,
Call Greater Thunder"!
[SHALLTEAR screams]
[AINS grunting]
[SHALLTEAR] He's undead!
Fire should have finished him.
[SHALLTEAR]
Let me guess.
You used magic to protect
yourself against fire.
[AINS] Compensating for
your weaknesses is basic.
[SHALLTEAR] True, but he can't
prepare countermeasures
for all elemental weaknesses.
In that case, I'll have
to stick with the element
that hurts him most.
"Cast Maximize Magic,
Brilliant Radiance"!
[AINS]
"Maximize Magic, True Dark"!
[groaning]
[AINS groaning]
Looks like holy
magic really does
a number on you!
[AINS groaning]
Cocytus! What's
happening to him?
[COCYTUS] The holy element
is a fatal weakness.
Even to undead of
Lord Ains' level.
Since his equipment focuses
mainly on protection from fire,
he has no way of guarding
himself against it completely.
[panting]
[SHALLTEAR] I used one holy
spell after another against him.
But, in a battle of magic,
Lord Ains is still far superior.
Thankfully, I've managed to
make his MP drop quite a bit.
[AINS]
"Body of Effulgent Beryl."
Must be defensive magic.
Good. I was bored anyway.
It will be much more fun to
rip you apart with my lance!
[AINS]
You truly have me cornered.
Huh? Then why
don't you run away?
At this point, it seems like
your only chance for survival.
[AINS]
You might be right about that.
But, truth be told,
I don't care.
I'm a selfish man, and
stubborn beyond measure.
I don't want to run.
It's funny.
I feel strangely fulfilled
as guild leader.
But, given the
current circumstances,
I don't quite
understand why that is.
Perhaps no one can.
Maybe it's because
that, while I held
the position of guild leader,
I mainly dealt with
day-to-day business
and administrating regulations.
But, right now, I am fighting
on the frontlines for my guild.
It may just be
self-satisfaction.
So it's pride?
Here I thought you were
beyond such human feelings.
[AINS] Who knows? You might
be right about that.
Look at me, I've really
dampened the mood
with this, haven't I? Why
don't we continue our duel?
Now, "Summon Household"!
[AINS]
"Sharks Cyclone"!
[SHALLTEAR yells]
[AINS yells]
[AINS groans]
[SHALLTEAR]
Heh.
[AINS] "Body of Effulgent
Beryl, Activate"!
[gasps]
[AINS]
"Wall of Skeletons"!
"Maximize Magic,
Force Explosion"!
[gasps]
[AINS]
"Greater Magic Seal, Release"!
[yelps]
"Magic Destruction"!
[AINS]
"Fly"!
She recovered!
"Triple Maximize Magic,
Reality Slash"!
[SHALLTEAR grunts]
"Negative Impact Shield"!
[AINS]
At last. She's using it.
Shalltear's final trump card.
[AINS]
Einherjar!
"Summon Household."
[MOMONGA] These numbers
are a bit of a problem.
But one well-placed spell should
be enough to take them out.
Einherjar, on the
other hand, will be--
[AINS gasps]
[MOMONGA]
That's so cheap!
I know friendly fire is
allowed, but I can't believe
she'd sacrifice her
household to heal herself!
[AINS groans]
[AINS grunting]
[AINS] "Skill, The Goal
of All Life is Death"!
"Widen Magic"!
"Cry of the Banshee"!
[gasps, growls]
[clock chimes]
[clock ticking]
[AINS]
Game over.
[AINS] That must have been
quite an experience.
How did you enjoy your first
foray into death, Shalltear?
[SHALLTEAR] I expected
no less of you, my lord.
For a moment, I actually
thought I would share
in my household's dark fate.
But, thanks to the resurrection
item Lord Peroroncino
gave me, my HP is at max,
and I'm fresh as a daisy
and ready to go another round.
However, your MP should be
running on empty, meaning
your offensive ability
is next to nothing.
And, whatever spell
you can muster
would never take my
HP down from full.
[AINS]
You're right.
[SHALLTEAR] Still, you
were amazing, and I also
have no MP left.
I had to use my
most powerful skills
just to keep you
on the defensive.
I couldn't imagine
it would be possible
for it to have been
a closer match.
For being at a disadvantage,
you did very well
to get this far.
[AINS] Honest praise.
I'll accept it graciously.
Now then.
Do you have any last
words before I end you?
[AINS]
Let's see.
I suppose I could go
on and on about how
I'm defenseless without my MP.
Or I could commend
you for so expertly
backing me into a corner.
Instead, I think I'll
thank you for fighting me
with everything you had.
And ensuring my victory.
[gasps]
[AINS] If you had fought
me any other way,
I would have never been able to
execute my plan so flawlessly.
[AINS] Shalltear's powerful,
heavy attacks have taken my MP
down to nothing.
She grins, assured
of her victory.
I suppose this is
as good a time as any
to bring my plan to light.
Everything is revealed.
I am the Overlord!
The one who rules over
the Tomb of Nazarick!
Face me and you face the
power of Ains Ooal Gown!
You will see it soon enough!
Chapter 13: "Player VS.
Non Player Character."