This girl is harmless.
"Cast Twin Maximize Magic"!
What?!
"Electrosphere"!
[KHAJIT cackles]
Impressive.
How annoying.
Why don't you just
roll over and die
like a good little rodent?
I guess those men
I killed in town
were friends of yours,
is that right?
Did you come here
to avenge them,
or something
stupid like that?
[giggles] Did you notice
the magic caster
was really a girl?
She kept insisting
that someone would
come to rescue them.
But I got bored
of waiting around.
[AINS]
I barely knew those adventurers.
I can't get hard
if you're not angry.
[AINS]
This isn't vengeance.
They were in your way and
needed to be dealt with.
I would have done the
same thing in your shoes.
It would be hypocritical
to condemn you.
That being said, by killing
them, you've robbed me
of valuable assets.
They were vital
components in my plans.
In other words...
You're in my way!
[growls] You must not
have a brain underneath
that helm of yours if you
think you can talk to me
like that and get away with it.
The inhuman Lady
Clementine doesn't
lose brawls to
nobodies like you.
You're about to learn
why people fear me!
[AINS]
I see nothing to be scared of.
You're a joke.
Now shut up and fight!
[KHAJIT] You might be skilled,
but it won't save you, fool.
Careful. That mouth will
get you into trouble,
human tick.
I'll call you a fool
if I like, little girl.
You've leapt into your doom
and don't realize it.
Now you're in the land of
the dead--my territory.
And soon you will join my army.
That's the fate of all who stand
between me and immortality!
[AINS]
Keep an eye on the sky.
[gasps]
[NARBERAL grunts]
[roars]
[laughs]
[KHAJIT This Skeletal
Dragon is completely
resistant to magic.
There isn't a caster in
the world that could hope
to stand against it.
Your death is a certainty.
Huh?
[NARBERAL] If that's the case,
I'll beat it to death.
[NARBERAL grunts]
[SKELETAL DRAGON 9A groans]
[gasps] What? But, how?
[KHAJIT]
What are you? Answer me!
Mythril rank?
No, you'd have to be
orichalcum to pull that off!
Well...
You truly are an insect
if a love tap like that
makes you quiver with fear.
It's sad, really.
Bitch! I'll kill you!
[KHAJIT] You can't stop me!
I won't allow it!
Show her the folly
of her stupidity!
[gasps]
[roars]
"Reinforce Armor."
"Spell of Lesser Strength."
"Shield Wall." "Undead Flame"!
"Reinforce Armor."
"Shield Wall."
"Protection from
Negative Energy."
[KHAJIT growls]
[NARBERAL grunts]
[grunts]
"Acid Javelin"!
Defensive magic?
How troublesome.
[NARBERAL]
"Chain Lightning"!
[gasps]
[roars]
I'm the one this is
troublesome for,
you bagworm. Why don't
you stop hiding
behind that dragon?
[KHAJIT grunts] Guess it can't
be helped. Jewel of Death!
Take a good look. This is
my terrifying power!
[roars]
A second one?
Well, it seems I've had to
use all the negative energy
I collected thus far.
Only a minor setback.
Once I kill you and bring
death to E-Rantel,
it will be replenished tenfold.
[laughing]
Uh?
[NARBERAL grunting]
[SKELETAL DRAGONS growling]
[gasping]
[grunting]
Just who in the hell are you?
How can you have
such physical strength
without the aid of
a martial arts skill?
[NARBERAL] I was created by
Supreme Beings even the Gods
of this world couldn't fathom.
[KHAJIT]
Are you mocking me, girl?
So, you can't even
understand the truth
when you hear it. Pathetic worm.
[CLEMENTINE laughs]
What?
Don't tell me you're
getting tired already.
[CLEMENTINE] You've got plenty
in the strength department,
I'll give you that much.
I can see why you'd
wanna boast about it.
Still, I have to ask.
Are you dumb?
You swing those things around
like a brainless meathead
who's just hoping
to hit something.
Are you sure you're a warrior?
[AINS] It's hard to tell if all
you're going to do is dodge.
Why don't you attack
me and find out?
[CLEMENTINE]
Believe me, I'd like to.
[AINS] I thought you said
you could beat any warrior.
Where'd your confidence go?
[SKELETAL DRAGON 9A roars]
[CLEMENTINE giggles]
[AINS]
Skeletal Dragons.
Correct! You sure
know your stuff.
Your cute little caster friend
is helpless against them,
since they're immune to magic.
[AINS]
I see.
She's doomed to fail,
is that right?
You catch on quick.
[AINS]
I'm curious.
Do you have a way to get
past the reach of my swords?
Maybe.
[CLEMENTINE sighs]
[AINS grunts]
[AINS]
Hm?
--[CLEMENTINE laughs]
--[AINS grunts]
[CLEMENTINE]
"Impenetrable Fortress."
[AINS grunts]
[gasps]
[AINS]
Martial arts.
That's a hard shell to
crack. Well, no matter.
Finding the weakest spot in
someone's armor is half the fun.
It's almost like foreplay.
Still, I was hoping
I could slice you up
piece by agonizing piece until
you couldn't move anymore.
Can't always get what you want.
[AINS] So, you were
just testing my armor.
I'm learning a lot from you.
[CLEMENTINE]
Ready for round two?
[AINS grunts]
"Impenetrable Fortress."
"Flow acceleration"!
[gasps]
[AINS grunts]
Come on, get serious.
If you keep giving
me a handicap,
you'll end up a corpse.
[AINS]
Goodness.
I hadn't expected you
to teach me this much
about melee combat.
Like the importance of
balancing your attacks,
and properly utilizing
martial arts skills.
Huh? You just learned that?
What kind of warrior are you?
More importantly, why didn't
you take any damage
after my attack hit home?
Tell me. Was it a defense skill?
[AINS]
You have my gratitude.
I wish I could stay and see
what else you have to offer.
Sadly, I can't afford
to wait any longer.
I'm afraid playtime has to end.
Huh?
[AINS]
Narberal Gamma!
Show them the power of Nazarick!
What the hell?
[AINS] Now. Steel yourself
for death and come at me.
[panting]
[KHAJIT laughs]
Surrender now, and I might
decide to be merciful.
Humans are too cocky.
What was that?
You should learn
your rightful place--
Beneath us.
Crush her, Skeletal Dragons!
[SKELETAL DRAGONS roar]
--[AINS] Narberal Gamma!
--[gasps]
Huh?
[AINS]
Show them the power of Nazarick!
Uh--
As you wish, my lord.
I will no longer
fight you as Nabe.
Now you face Narberal
Gamma of the Pleiades.
[SKELETAL DRAGONS roar]
"Teleportation."
[gasps]
Now, "Fly."
[KHAJIT]
She vanished? Where did she go?
[gasps]
She's even able
to cast flying magic?
But, still, she didn't have
time to dodge their attack.
What's she doing?
This is a perfect
chance to escape.
Why isn't she running
for her life?
She can't possibly
think she has a chance
of overcoming complete
magical resistance!
There are plenty of ways
that I can defeat your
dragons. I'll show you.
[NARBERAL]
Rejoice, human.
You have the honor of facing
a servant to the absolute ruler
of the Great Tomb of Nazarik.
The Supreme Being and rightful
Overlord of this world,
Lord Ains Ooal Gown.
You are fortunate.
As a member of the
Pleiades battle maids,
I will be your opponent.
A maid?
[growls]
Skeletal Dragons!
[SKELETAL DRAGONS growl]
She's gone!
[groans]
Does it hurt that badly?
[KHAJIT grunts]
That was your trump card.
You hid your teleportation
magic so you could kill me
when my guard was down.
[NARBERAL]
Of course not, worm.
I was just showing you
that I could kill you easily.
Your dragons will
be no different.
Insane. You're out of your mind!
[NARBERAL] I didn't expect
an insignificant flea
like you to understand.
Still, your reply is pitiful.
[KHAJIT]
How dare you.
[NARBERAL]
It's time I ended this farce.
After all, if I made
my lord wait too long,
what kind of maid would I be?
Do you truly believe
these dragons of yours
are immune to magic?
You have a lot to learn
about being a caster.
I'll have you pay for this
lesson with your pathetic life.
[gasps] What kind
of magic is that?
Try it. They're both
still immune.
Nothing you throw
at them will matter!
[NARBERAL]
Not completely immune.
To be more precise, their
magical resistance nullifies
any spells that are
sixth tier and below.
But I'm able to cast
even higher tiered magic.
If you're still having
trouble understanding,
that means I can beat
your pets with ease.
You are crazy.
No one in this world can
cast seventh tier magic.
That power belongs to the gods!
[SKELETAL DRAGONS roar]
[chuckles]
Five years. Countless schemes.
All my meticulous planning
and preparations for tonight.
I refuse to believe it
will be taken from me
by a girl in a maid outfit!
Your death will serve my master.
You should take comfort in that.
"Twin Maximize Magic."
"Chain Dragon Lightning"!
[SKELETAL DRAGONS roar]
[KHAJIT gasps]
[KHAJIT screams]
It seems even
insects smell tasty
when they're roasted.
I'll give this to
Entoma as a souvenir.
[CLEMENTINE]
That's an interesting tactic.
Are you giving up?
[AINS] I think I should
finish up, as well.
It wouldn't be fair
to Narberal, otherwise.
Wow. You're one cocky bastard.
You don't have a single
martial arts skill,
and you think you can beat
the great Lady Clementine?
Congrats, now I'm
royally pissed off.
[AINS] Are you going to
keep raving or actually
do something about it?
[growls] Y'know,
you're right, we should
finish things up here.
"Stride of Wind."
"Greater Evasion."
"Ability Boost."
"Greater Ability Boost"!
[CLEMENTINE]
He's not moving?
Die!
I'm not finished with you yet!
[CLEMENTINE laughing]
[CLEMENTINE gasping]
[AINS]
Hm. Interesting.
There wasn't a weapon
like this in Yggdrasil.
I'll watch out for them.
What? No way! You
shouldn't be alive!
[AINS] I guess there's
no point hiding it.
[CLEMENTINE]
An Undead? You're an Elder Lich?
[AINS] Well. You're
only partially right.
I'm curious. How did
you like fighting
a sword-wielding
magic caster?
You bastard!
What...
...the hell?
[AINS] This is why I
gave you a handicap.
You're all bark.
There was no need for
me to fight a mongrel
of your level seriously.
If I had cast the weakest
spell I know to defeat you,
it would have been
a waste of MP.
[screams]
[AINS]
What's the matter, bitch?
Did you not like my answer?
These are in the way.
You've... gotta be kidding!
[AINS]
All right. Let's begin.
No way.
Stop it. Stop it!
[AINS] I had considered
killing you with this.
It would have been poetic
justice at its finest.
Then again, death by blade.
Death by broken bones.
Death by crushing.
There's really not much
difference, is there?
In the end, you die.
[whimpers]
[CLEMENTINE]
Let go, you bastard!
[AINS]
Stop your squirming.
[CLEMENTINE growling]
[AINS] You took your time
killing her, didn't you?
[CLEMENTINE growling, groaning]
[AINS] It's only fair to give
you the same treatment.
Slow and painful.
[AINS]
I've enjoyed this dance.
I forgot to tell you.
Try as I might, I have a
tendency to be... hypocritical.
[FOREST KING]
Master! Master!
[yelps] That's not master!
It's a monster!
[NARBERAL]
Annoying gerbil.
I do not see what you do
in this creature, my lord.
He is foolish and unworthy.
[AINS]
That's enough.
The fact that he is the
Wise King of the Forest
makes him a valuable asset.
We have more important
matters to tend do.
Take anything valuable or
useful from the corpses
before the soldiers and
other adventurers arrive.
[NARBERAL]
Right!
Shall we take their bodies
to Nazarick for testing?
[AINS]
No.
We need to hand them
over to the authorities
so they have someone
to blame for all of this.
We'll just take their
equipment this time.
As you wish, my master.
[AINS] I can easily cure
his blindness with
healing magic, but...
As for his mind, the control
over it will be tricky to break.
This is definitely the source.
[AINS]
"All Appraisal Magic Item."
[AINS] The Crown of
Wisdom. Interesting.
It seems to be an item
that can't be
replicated in Yggdrasil.
Ideally, I'd like to take
him back to Nazarick.
But I took this
job on good faith.
A deliberate failure would dirty
the name of Ains Ooal Gown.
Crumble away.
"Greater Break Item"!
[NARBERAL]
Lord Ains.
Master. Please, forgive me.
Serve you with even greater
conviction, I shall!
[AINS]
That's great, Hamusuke. Anyway.
Let's complete the job!
[FOREST KING]
Master!
Please don't take
my pledge so lightly!
Hurt my delicate
feelings, it does!
[AINS] I thought they'd
promote us to orichalcum,
but I suppose this will do.
[NARBERAL]
Their insolence knows no bounds.
[AINS]
It's fine, Nabe.
As we speak, the surviving
soldiers are spreading
the tale of my strength and
valor to everyone in E-Rantel.
The boost that will
give to my status makes
getting mythril rank
a moot point.
Very well.
What should we do about
the boy and his grandmother?
[AINS] Since Lizzy said that
she would give me everything,
I'll have her and Nphiera
move to Carne Village.
Her skill at making
potions will serve me--
or rather all of Nazarick--
quite well. Hm...
Oh, right. I needed
to contact Albedo.
--"Message."
--[beeps]
[ALBEDO]
Lord Ains.
I'm afraid I must report
that Shalltear Bloodfallen
has betrayed us.
[AINS]
Huh?
[AINS] While I was living
among the humans
as the adventurer, Momon,
my faithful Guardians
worked diligently at
their respective roles.
Shalltear Bloodfallen's job
was to collect special humans
that could use magic
and martial arts skills.
With Sebas at her side, I had
ordered her to target criminals
and other lowlife scum.
That way, they would
be missed by no one.
Chapter ten: "True Vampire."