[HEAD PRIEST]
Nigun Grid Luwin.
As captain of the
Sunlit Scripture,
one of the six scriptures
of the Six Great Gods, you
are called upon to serve.
[NIGUN]
With honor.
[HEAD PRIEST] You will go
to the Re-Estize Kingdom.
Locate Gazef Stronoff,
and eliminate him.
[grunts]
[HEAD PRIEST] This treasure
contains a miracle of the Gods.
Use it only if necessary.
[NIGUN]
Attention, all units.
Our prey has entered the cage.
Devote yourself to the Gods,
and carry out their will.
[GAZEF]
There they are.
It looks like
they've surrounded us
in equal intervals.
[AINS] Do you have some
idea of who they are?
Only the Slane Theocracy
could send out
this many magic casters at once.
And they're part of
a special ops unit
directly under the Head Priest.
It must be one of
the six scriptures.
[AINS] Then the men who attacked
the village earlier...?
Theocracy soldiers, no doubt.
Looks like they dressed in
Imperial armor to throw us off.
[AINS]
As I thought.
Does this village hold
some significant value?
If you don't know
why they're attacking,
then I'm assuming
they're not after you,
which means one thing.
[AINS] It would appear that
you are quite despised,
Chief Warrior.
Indeed. Well, lucky me.
To think, even the Slane
Theocracy wants me dead.
[MOMONGA] But those creatures
look like Archangel Flames.
Why is a monster
from Yggdrasil here?
[GAZEF] Sir Ains.
I would like to hire you.
Name your price and I'll
make sure you get it.
[AINS]
Sorry, but I have to decline.
Very well.
Then, please take care
and thanks again.
This village owes
you gratitude. As do I.
[AINS grunts]
I am grateful, which is
why I hesitate to ask.
I know this is
a selfish request.
Please, grant these people
your protection one more time.
I have nothing to offer
you now, but, I beg you.
Please--
[AINS] There is no need for
you to go that far, Gazef.
I understand. I will be sure
to protect the villagers.
I will even put the name of
Ains Ooal Gown on the line.
Then, I will have
nothing to worry about.
Instead, I will focus
on the task before me.
[AINS]
Take this. I insist.
[gasps] You're giving me a gift?
I gratefully accept it.
Thanks.
[AINS]
Good luck.
Ha!
[AINS sighs] When I first
met the humans here,
I saw them as no more
than insects, as you do.
But, the more I speak with
them, the fonder I grow.
Like a child among
helpless animals.
[ALBEDO] Is that the reason
you were willing to promise
the honor of your great name
to his request, my lord?
[AINS]
Perhaps.
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
Lord Ains!
Those marauders are
still out there.
Why is the Chief
Warrior leaving?
[AINS] Because he was their
true target, not the village.
Then, should we just
stay here and wait
for him to deal
with those brigands?
[AINS]
That would be unwise.
Once the Chief Warrior and
his men disrupt their lines,
we will make our escape.
He will cause as much
commotion as he can
to make a clear path for us.
[BOTH sigh]
We'll attack them head on!
Break through the soldiers
and lead the enemy
away from the villagers!
After that, continue to retreat!
Timing is crucial here!
[SUBORDINATES]
Understood, sir!
Now, then.
Let's paint the ground with
their God-loving guts!
[SUBORDINATES yell]
[yells]
[grunts]
Here, sir!
Uh?
[yells]
Tough, aren't you?
"Martial Art."
[GAZEF]
"Focus Battle Aura"!
[GAZEF grunts]
[GAZEF]
Magic really pisses me off.
All right. It's done.
This is all according to plan.
It's up to you, Sir Ains.
[SUBORDINATES yelling]
Huh?
Stay by Gazef's side...!
[SUBORDINATE 4B]
We're the ones who will protect
this country!
[SUBORDINATES yelling]
I told you to retreat!
What are you doing
coming back for me?
You're all damn fools.
But your fools I'm
proud to fight beside.
[SLANE PRIESTS]
Huh?
[SUBORDINATES yelp]
[SUBORDINATE 4B groans]
[SUBORDINATES gasp]
[SUBORDINATES grunting, yelling]
There's too many. They'll
completely overtake us.
[GAZEF] But, if we take out
their commander, it's all over!
Come on! You're in my way!
"Martial Art, Six-Fold
Slash of Light"!
[SUBORDINATES gasp, laugh]
"Martial Art, Instant Counter"!
"Flow..."
[GAZEF]
"...Acceleration"!
[grunts]
Ya see that?
We can win!
[pants]
[NIGUN]
Impressive.
Mastering that many
skills isn't easy.
Sadly, it won't save you.
Summon another set of angels.
Focus all of your magical
attacks on the Chief Warrior.
We're in trouble.
I'm scared!
[NEMU sobs]
It's all right. Trust me.
[grunting]
[GAZEF pants]
[GAZEF groans]
[NIGUN] Finish him off.
But don't leave it to chance.
Attack with all of them
to ensure his fate.
[growling]
I'm... not... through... yet!
I am the Chief Warrior!
My heart and soul
belong to Re-Estize!
I'll die 1,000 times before
I lose to the likes of you!
Yes, you will die,
and you'll only have
your blaspheming tongue
to blame for it.
Face it, Gazef Stronoff.
There's nothing you
can do to stop us.
Once we're through with you,
we'll massacre the villagers.
Cease your futile resistance,
and just lie down
like a good dog.
As an act of mercy,
I'll make sure
your death is painless.
[laughs]
Is something amusing?
Yeah, you and your little army.
When the man in the
village comes for you,
it will be a massacre.
Trying to bluff me?
Kill him, angels.
Make sure he suffers.
[AINS] Looks like it's
time for us to switch.
[VILLAGERS gasp, murmur]
Huh? Where am I?
[VILLAGE CHIEF] This is the
village storage house.
Lord Ains set up
a magical barrier
to keep us all safe.
Is he here?
He was, but he just vanished
right in front of our eyes.
Then you appeared in his place.
[gasps]
I'll be...
[clatter]
And just who are you?
[AINS] Nice to meet you,
people of the Slane Theocracy.
My name is Ains Ooal Gown.
But, please, call me Ains.
[AINS] I have something
of a relationship
with those villagers.
Have you come to
beg for their lives,
or just your own?
[AINS]
No, no. You misunderstand.
[SLANE PRIESTS]
Hm?
[AINS]
I overheard your conversation
with the Chief Warrior.
You really have a lot
of balls, don't you?
Huh?
[AINS] I spent my
precious time and energy
saving those people,
and you brazenly declared
your intent to massacre them.
I can't imagine
anything more offensive.
You're being rather
brazen yourself,
for a meager magic caster.
So, what do you plan to do?
[AINS] Offer your pitiful life
to me without resistance.
Do this and there
will be no pain.
However, if you refuse,
I swear, here and now,
you will die painfully and in
despair for your imprudence.
Have the angels
attack this fool!
[gasps] Is that all you had?
I expected more after
a bluff like that.
Huh?
[AINS]
Did you not hear me?
I said to offer your
life without resistance.
By the time I'm
through with you,
you'll wish you had listened.
[SLANE PRIEST 4C]
A trick!
[SLANE PRIEST 4D]
Yes! It has to be!
[AINS] High Tiered
Physical Nullification.
It's a passive skill
that completely nullifies
the physical attacks
of low-leveled
weapons and monsters.
[gasps]
[AINS yells]
[AINS]
As I thought.
They really are the Archangel
Flames from Yggdrasil.
[AINS] The fact that you can
use magic and summon spells
from Yggdrasil intrigues me.
I want to know why
they exist here,
and how you could
have learned them.
But, for now, I'll
focus on killing you.
It's my turn.
You wanted a massacre?
You'll get one.
Don't just stand there.
Attack him! Hurry!
[AINS]
Albedo, stand back.
[ALBEDO]
Lord.
[AINS]
"Negative Burst"!
[SLANE PRIESTS gasping]
[gasps] That's not... possible!
[GAZEF] When the man in
the village comes for you,
it will be a massacre.
[SLANE PRIESTS shouting spells]
[AINS]
Hm.
It would seem they know
more Yggdrasil spells
than I initially thought.
Tell me! Where did
you learn that magic?
[SLANE PRIEST 4A yelping]
What just happened?
[AINS]
Albedo.
You're well aware that these
pitiful, low-level spells
would have done me no harm.
There was no need
for you to interfere.
[ALBEDO]
I beg your pardon, Lord Ains.
but if someone wishes
to fight a Supreme Being,
such as you, they should
at least be able to best me.
These men are mere pebbles
fighting a mountain.
[AINS laughs] I'm afraid they
wouldn't meet your requirements
in ten lifetimes.
Now...
Principality of
Observation! Attack!
[AINS] My, my. I guess
I should fight back.
"Hell Flame."
[SLANE PRIESTS gasping]
[NIGUN]
That was... one hit!
That's impossible!
There's no way a high level
angel could be destroyed
using only one spell!
[SLANE PRIEST 4C]
Captain Nigun, sir!
What should we do now?
We'll summon the
highest-level angel!
[SLANE PRIESTS gasp]
[MOMONGA]
Is that...?
[MOMONGA] Based on how it
glows, it's a sealing crystal
that can hold any magic
other than top tier spells.
So, they even have
Yggdrasil items.
[AINS] Albedo. I believe
your skills may be required.
[ALBEDO]
Understood!
Behold! The shining form
of the highest of angels!
Dominion Authority!
[SLANE PRIESTS cheer]
[AINS]
Wait.
You're telling me this is
your strongest trump card?
That's right.
I didn't think I'd have to call
on it, but you proved worthy
of its divine greatness!
[AINS] I'm at a complete
loss for words.
Regretting your folly?
I wouldn't blame
you if you were.
[AINS]
This is stupid.
What?
[AINS] I can't believe
I put up my guard
for this sort of child's play.
What was that?
You can't be serious!
No way. You're, lying!
Mankind can't compete
with its might!
I'll show you!
Smite him with
your divine power!
Dominion Authority
is the holy product
of seventh tier magic!
Nothing can survive it!
Now, receive the Gods'
judgment and repent!
[AINS laughs]
Huh?
[AINS laughing]
[AINS] So this is how it feels
to take damage. This is pain!
[gasping]
[ALBEDO growling]
[AINS gasps]
[ALBEDO]
You lower life form!
[screams]
[ALBEDO]
That's my love!
My beloved Lord Ains, the
ruler of my heart and soul!
You caused him pain!
And for that,
you will know hell!
[AINS]
Calm down, Albedo.
[ALBEDO]
But, Lord Ains!
[AINS]
It's fine.
Aside from the surprising
weakness of the angels,
everything is going exactly
as I had foreseen it.
[AINS] It's my turn
again. Know despair!
"Black Hole"!
[SLANE PRIESTS gasp]
[NIGUN] Even demons don't
have this kind of power.
Just who in the world are you?
[AINS]
Ains Ooal Gown.
In the past, there
was no one alive
who did not fear this name.
Hey, what was that?
[AINS]
It seems that someone was using
reconnaissance magic
to watch you from afar.
I'm guessing the Theocracy.
But my defense barrier
counteracted it,
so I doubt they saw very much.
My country was watching me?
[AINS] If that's all you had,
it's time to end this.
[NIGUN]
No! No, no, no please, wait!
I beg of you, Sir Ains. I mean,
Lord Ains! Spare my life!
The rest of these
men don't matter!
[SLANE PRIESTS yell]
[NIGUN] I'll give you
anything you wish! Name it!
I will do whatever it
takes to appease you!
[ALBEDO]
I think you're confused.
Huh?
[ALBEDO] Lord Ains has
no need for sniveling
lower life forms. Humans like
you should bow their heads
and give thanks to him for
ending their miserable lives.
What's that mean,
"humans like me"?
[AINS]
What was it you said to Gazef?
"Cease your futile resistance
and just lie down
like a good dog."
As an act of mercy,
I'll make sure your
death is painless."
[MOMONGA]
I wonder...
Did I live up to
Albedo's expectations
as the Lord of Nazarick?
So cool! Lord Ains
is such a badass.
[AINS]
Hm? Did you say something?
[ALBEDO]
Hm? Nothing, my lord.
But, if I may ask, why did
you save that human soldier?
You even gave him
that important relic.
[MOMONGA]
Actually, it was a gimmick item
from a lottery machine.
More importantly, you
could have sent me
to fight in your place.
I am your shield.
There was no need to personally
risk your life like that.
[AINS]
I know your strength, Albedo,
and I trust your devotion.
However, until we know
more about this world,
we must proceed with
the utmost caution.
Believing the enemy is stronger
than us keeps us safe.
So you tested their power
by using him as a pawn!
Your use of humans is
truly impeccable, my lord.
Uh, however...
I fail to see how taking
that last angel's attack
head on counted as "caution."
[AINS]
Is that so?
Watching you feel pain
was more than I could bare.
I knew you would come through
it unscathed, but still.
No woman wants her
true love to get hurt!
[AINS]
Oh, right.
Let's go home, Albedo.
[ALBEDO]
With pleasure, Lord Ains!
[AINS]
Everyone.
I want to apologize for
leaving the Tomb on my own.
There will be time
to fill you in
on all that has happened.
However, there is a
more pressing matter
I want to attend to.
"Greater Break Item"!
[GUARDIANS gasp]
[AINS]
I have changed my name.
From this day forward,
I will be known as:
Ains Ooal Gown!
You shall call me Ains!
If you have any objections,
stand and voice them!
We have heard your
precious name, lord.
And devote ourselves to it
with unwavering loyalty.
Glory to Lord Ains Ooal Gown!
[GUARDIANS] Glory to Lord
Ains Ooal Gown! All hail!
We give ourselves to you,
utterly and without
any hesitation!
[BOTH] To the most
powerful Supreme Being!
Everyone in this world will know
of your greatness, and
fear your undying wrath.
[COCYTUS] Our king, who
rules over all, forever.
Glory to the Overlord,
the supreme ruler of death!
[AINS]
This is an absolute order!
Make the name Ains Ooal
Gown an eternal legend!
[GUARDIANS cheer]
[MOMONGA] Across the land,
through the sky,
and over the sea.
I will spread the name
of Ains Ooal Gown
to every corner of
this strange new world.
If any of my friends
have come here as well,
they'll know they're
not alone and find me.
[ALBEDO] Demiurge,
please tell everyone about
your conversation
with the master.
I was with Lord Ains
the first night we arrived
in this world and
he told me this:
"The stars glitter like jewels.
I was sent to this land to
obtain those jewels for myself,
along with every treasure
that shines beneath them."
Then, after a moment,
I heard him say:
"The most enjoyable
thing now might be
taking over the world." Yes.
[ALBEDO]
Hear that?
Let it be known, here and now,
that this is our final goal.
As servants of the
Tomb of Nazarick,
we will present this
world to Lord Ains,
without fail!
[GUARDIANS cheer]
[AINS]
In order to collect information
about this new world, there's a
need to live among the humans.
To this end, I've hidden my
skeleton body in a suit of armor
and entered the Adventurer's
Guild under the name "Momon"
with Narberal at
my side as "Nabe."
If I make a name
for myself here,
I'll be able to make some money
and gather vauable intel.
It's a completely perfect plan.
But I couldn't have foreseen
that even Narberal hated
humans so pasionately.
Chapter five: "Two Venturers."