[door creaks]
[CLEMENTINE] It's about
time you showed up,
I was starting to get worried
something bad had happened.
Shame on you for making me wait.
Oh, sorry.
The shop will open
in the morning.
Hey! Do you not know
who this woman is?
[CLEMINTINE cackles]
'Course he doesn't.
Or he'd be running away.
Huh?
Nphirea! Get behind us.
Your affinity for
magical items is exactly
what I need for my plans.
I want you to summon an army
of the undead just for me.
What?
Whether you like it or not,
you'll wear the Crown of Wisdom.
So you might as well come along.
It'll be fun. Whaddya say?
Who the hell are you?
[CLEMENTINE]
I'm the last person
who's going to see
you boys alive.
After you've all suffered
a slow and painful demise,
your friend and I are
going to cast a spell.
We're going to release
an undead army together.
There's no way to
control the amount
of creatures that I'm planning
on raising from the grave,
so be prepared for utter chaos.
I've waited so long
for this power!
[yells]
Leave now. Run away
as fast as you can.
I can't.
Ninya. You need to flee as well.
Huh?
Take the boy and go!
We won't allow this lady
to capture either of you.
They're right.
Your big sister
is counting on you
to rescue her from
those aristocrats.
Slip away while you
still have a chance.
You guys...
[laughs] This is just
the saddest scene.
As if anyone could escape.
There's not even the slightest
chance that it could happen.
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
Stop playing around.
[CLEMENTINE whines]
Oh, all right, fine,
but did you place the spell
that will cover
up their screams?
I'd like to take my
sweet time playing with
one of them at the
very least. 'Kay?
[whimpers]
[NINYA]
Save us, Momon.
[AINS]
Sorry that took so long.
I don't mind waiting.
[AINS]
The request was approved.
From now on, you shall
be called Hamusuke.
Take great pride
in the name, I shall.
It talks!
[gasps]
How cute!
How can a copper plate
even afford that creature?
Well, I've heard that
he's wearing a disguise.
And he's actually
a famous adventurer.
[LIZZY]
Hey, I know you.
Aren't you the man my grandson
hired to accompany him
on his herb gathering trip?
[AINS]
Hm?
I am Nphirea's grandmother.
The pharmacist Lizzy Ballear.
[AINS]
Oh, yes.
You are correct, we were
the ones who traveled
to Carne Village with him.
I am Momon and this
is my partner Nabe.
This animal is--
Hamusuke. My name, it is.
The Wise King of the
Forest, I used to be.
Absurd, you're an
overgrown rodent.
Am I supposed to believe
this is the legendary
King of the Forest?
[FOREST KING]
Mm-hm!
[AINS]
It is.
He was out of control
and confronted us
during our mission
with your grandson.
But I beat him into submission.
Shocking. Did Nphirea
make it back okay?
[AINS] Yes, he should be at the
store by now with his herbs.
We were about to make our
way over there to collect
the payment for a job well done.
That's where I'm heading.
Care to escort a fair maiden?
[AINS]
It would be my pleasure.
[LIZZY] Nphirea! Mr. Momon
is here for his reward.
Where is that boy hiding?
[AINS]
Something's not right.
[gasps] What's wrong?
[AINS]
Where does this lead?
To the room where we
store medicinal herbs.
[AINS gasps]
[LIZZY gasps]
These men have been murdered!
[ADVENTURERS groaning, growling]
They're zombies!
--[AINS grunts]
--[LUKURT, PETER groan]
[DYNE growls]
--[AINS grunts]
--[DYNE groans]
I don't see Nphirea.
[AINS]
That's because he's not here.
[LIZZY]
Nphirea!
[AINS]
Keep Lizzy safe.
[NARBERAL]
I'm right behind her.
[AINS]
Ninya.
[AINS] Why leave only
him alive? What the...
[LUKRUT]
"Throwing a girl into the mix
would be distracting."
[AINS]
So that's how it was.
Whoever did this... will pay.
[AINS]
Stabbed through the head.
[LIZZY] I've looked everywhere!
My grandson isn't here.
[AINS] It doesn't look like
the perpetrators stole
anything from their packs.
So that means Nphirea was
the only thing they came for.
Who were these poor
men that got killed?
[AINS] Adventurers that
came along with us
on your grandson's quest.
I'm sorry about your friends.
[AINS]
I barely knew them.
This was the first job
we ever did together.
Oh.
[AINS]
How do you want to handle this?
Whaddya mean?
[AINS]
You want to find Nphirea, right?
We're dealing with at least
a third tier spell caster.
One that decided to use
Create Undead on these men
instead of just
hiding the bodies.
Which is odd, since that
would have given them
a bigger head start.
The culprits were confident
that they would get away.
And wanted to advertise
the power they possess
and are willing to use.
These are dangerous people.
We need to act quickly
if we want to find them.
You need to make a request.
Huh?
[AINS] The right person
would make quick work
of this spellcaster.
What happened here
was a tragedy.
But you are lucky,
Ms. Lizzy Balear.
I happen to be the only
adventurer in town strong enough
to rescue your grandson.
And I'm currently
in between missions.
If you want to save
Nphirea, make a request
and I may just
accept your offer.
You can have whatever you want.
Just go save him,
bring my Nphirea home!
[AINS] I will. But my
services are not cheap.
Do you have the
means to pay my fee?
How much would you
charge an old lady?
[AINS]
Everything.
What?
[AINS]
I'll take all that you possess.
You fiend!
I've heard tales of demons
that make deals with humans
for their very souls.
Is that what you're
asking of me now?
Are you two really demons?
[AINS] Would you not be
willing to pay that price
for his life? It would
be a shame to lose
such a talented young man.
[growls]
[AINS] Time's ticking away
and I need an answer.
Make it quick.
You win. Consider
yourself hired, devil.
Take whatever you want from me.
[AINS] The first thing
we need to do is locate
where Nphirea is being held.
[NARBERAL]
How will we figure that out?
[AINS]
The criminals made one mistake.
Although they didn't
steal any valuables,
they took the time to remove
each man's adventurer plate.
Any guesses why that is?
The plates are worthless.
So I'm not sure.
--[AINS] I'll explain.
--[beeping]
[ENTOMA]
Lord Ains?
[AINS]
Entoma.
[ENTOMA]
I have some information.
[AINS]
You caught me at a bad time.
I'm in the middle
of something right now,
but I'll notify you
when I'm available.
[ENTOMA]
Certainly, master. Also,
Lady Albedo asks
that you contact her.
[AINS]
As I was saying.
The plates were taken
as hunting trophies.
I'm assuming the culprit
collects them as souvenirs.
Which is lucky for us
since we now have
something to track. We'll use
the Locate Object scroll.
[AINS]
You already know how to use it.
Let's find ourselves
some plates.
I'll activate it now.
[AINS]
Hold on.
The enemy may have set the
counter spell Detect Locate.
So we need to cast Fake Cover
and Counter Detection
to break through any defenses
they may have prepared.
[AINS]
Hm. There's no way
for them to hide from
all these spells.
So, start whenever
you're ready, Narberal.
"Fake Cover."
"Counter Detection."
[MOMONGA]
We have to be careful.
Collecting information
with magic is dangerous.
This encounter may
end in a Player Kill.
And if that happens, we need
to be overly prepared for it.
The Player's Handbook that
Punitto Moe wrote taught me
the importance of
attacking hard and fast.
[NARBERAL]
"Locate Object"!
Right here.
[AINS] That's in the
middle of the cemetery.
A fitting choice.
Please cast Clairvoyance
and Crystal Monitor
at the same time.
I want to see for myself.
"Clairvoyance"!
"Crystal Monitor"!
[AINS]
I see Nphirea. Among the undead.
And I can sense the ones
that stole the plates.
They are nearby.
What are your orders?
We could teleport there
and attack immediately.
Or use magic and launch
an assault from the sky.
[AINS]
Don't be foolish.
[gasps]
[AINS]
An army of the undead is ready
for such a reckless attack.
Whoever woke up that many
men from their graves
has something big planned
for them. That's good news.
Our names will spread far and
wide once we save Nphirea,
and stop whatever grand scheme
they're trying to pull.
[AINS] Unfortunately,
we have to move fast
and have no time to research
their plan further.
We've finished.
What have you discovered?
[AINS] They have fled
into the cemetery.
Is my grandson there?
[AINS]
Yes.
He's being guarded by a
large legion of the undead.
[gasps]
[AINS]
Don't be scared.
Nabe and I can handle
them, but a few undead
may escape the grounds.
That's why we need you
to let the townsfolk
and Adventurer's Guild
know what's happening.
We are headed to the cemetery
now, so you need to be quick.
Hold it. Just how do
you plan on defeating
such a large army of the undead?
[AINS]
With this weapon right here.
[SOLDIER 8A] Looks like
another uneventful night.
It's been awhile since
we've seen any action.
--Even the undead
--[groaning]
--have been quiet.
Huh? What was that noise?
Nice try, man, stop trying to--
Be quiet. I think
I heard it again.
It's just in your head.
[SOLDIER 8C]
Hey! Something's coming!
I don't believe it.
[SOLDIER 8A]
It's an entire army.
[CAPTAIN 8A] I've never seen
this many undead at once.
There's at least 1,000 of 'em!
Notify the reserves, quickly!
We'll try to hold them off
the gate until backup arrives.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[gasps, grunts]
Get... off me!
[UNDEAD 8B growls]
[SOLDIER 8D yelps]
[SOLDIER 8E grunts]
[SOLDIER 8F grunts]
[UNDEAD 8D growls]
[CAPTAIN 8A]
Damn! There's too many!
[CAPTIAN 8A]
Retreat!
Huh? An adventurer?
Thank goodness.
Damn, he's just a
useless copper plate!
Leave before you get killed!
[AINS]
Nabe. My sword.
Look up. You'll
want to see this.
[CAPTAIN 8A]
Huh?
[growling]
[AINS grunts]
[UNDEAD GIANT 8A groans]
[CAPTAIN 8A]
Uh... Who are you people?
[AINS]
Open the gate.
You have a death wish?
There's an entire legion of
undead on the other side!
[AINS]
I know.
Don't worry about a thing.
Momon is here to save you all.
Huh?
[AINS]
Fine then.
If you won't open the gate,
I'll just have to improvise.
[FOREST KING]
Don't worry 'bout me!
I'm right behind you, Lady Nabe!
Through thick and thin,
Hamusuke will be by your side!
That he shall!
[SOLDIERS, CAPTAIN 8A gasp]
[CAPTAIN 8A]
Wait. It can't be.
[gasps]
What is it?
The voices of the
undead just... stopped.
[SOLDIER 8B]
It's not possible.
There's no way they
defeated that many undead
all by themselves.
[SOLDIER 8C] That man.
What was his name again?
Momon, I think. I've never
heard of him before.
And we're sure he was
only a copper plate?
Seems wrong.
Well, I wonder if
he's the fabled
adamantite plate I've
heard rumors about.
[CAPTAIN 8A]
Whatever he is,
we just witnessed
a myth in the making.
The legend of a
raven black warrior
who becomes a hero!
[roars]
[AINS grunts]
--[UNDEAD groaning]
--[AINS grunting]
[FOREST KING]
So sorry.
Cause you this much trouble,
I did not mean to.
Stop wiggling around, will you?
It's hard enough to
carry you as it is.
[AINS] All undead creatures
are naturally drawn
towards the living.
If you were down here,
they'd try to overwhelm us.
So embarrassing, this is.
[UNDEAD ARMY groaning]
[AINS]
Damn.
It's going to take us forever
to cut through this pack.
I agree.
We should ask
Nahzahreek to send help.
[AINS]
Definitely not.
That would defeat
our entire purpose
for accepting this quest.
[NARBERAL]
If we wish to become renowned,
shouldn't we wait
for an incident
that claims more human lives?
People would have a greater
respect for our power
in a situation like that.
[AINS] The enemy's goal
is to take over the town.
The capital is too important
to be under the control
of an outlaw. I would
have approached
this situation differently
if I'd been better informed.
But there was no time to spare.
Yes, of course.
You are right as
usual, Lord Ains.
Please forgive me for
questioning your strategy.
I should have expected
this level of foresight
from a Supreme Being
like yourself.
By the way, would
you mind alleviating
my naivety on another
related matter?
I don't understand
why we didn't send in
forces with stealth
skills ahead of us.
They would have killed
most of the undead,
then we could have swooped
in and finished off
the strongest opponents
at our leisure.
[AINS] How will you ever
learn if I always tell you
the answer, Nabe? Try
figuring it out yourself!
Yes. I will endeavor to improve.
[AINS] That said, we don't
have time for leisure now.
We need to make a path.
And I think I know
what will do the trick.
"Summoning second tier
undead. Jack the Ripper"!
[JACK THE RIPPER cackles]
[AINS]
"Corpse Collector"!
[JACK THE RIPPER cackles]
[AINS]
Attack!
[JACK THE RIPPER cackles]
[CORPSE COLLECTOR roars]
Wow. Unstoppable, they are.
[AINS]
Now then. Let's continue.
[KHAJIT FOLLOWERS, KHAJIT
chanting] Mooway Oko Ube Doka...
[FOREST KING]
Master! Creepy place, it is.
Scared to be left alone, I am.
[KHAJIT FOLLOWER 8A]
Master Khajit, they're here.
[AINS]
Nice. Now I have a name.
Greetings! Are you
enjoying your night, Khajit?
[gasps, growls]
[gasps]
[AINS] Go have fun and
stop wasting your time
on a dull ritual.
[KHAJIT] Hmph. There's nothing
dull about this ritual.
As you'll soon witness.
Since you now know my name,
how about sharing yours?
[AINS] We're just adventurers
out doing a job.
I'm sure you've seen the
boy we're looking for.
Make it easy and show
us where he's hidden.
[KHAJIT FOLLOWERS gasp]
[AINS]
While you're at it,
point me in the direction
of your friend.
The one that carries
the piercing weapon.
Surely they're not too
scared to face me.
Or maybe they are only brave
enough to fight the weak?
[CLEMENTINE] You took the
time to examine the corpses.
Smart guy.
Go back in.
Khaji, this fella
has figured us out.
There's no point
in hiding anymore.
Aw, come on.
Don't you wanna tell sweet
lil' ole' me your name?
Huh? My name's Clementine.
The pleasure's mine.
[AINS] I'm your executioner.
Call me Momon.
Oh! You're confident.
Tell me, how you figured out
that we came to the cemetery?
[AINS]
Why, it was you who led us here.
Open up your cloak.
Whoa! Hey!
Now you're making me blush.
And I like it.
Looking for these?
[AINS] Those plates are
the reason I was able
to track you so easily.
[AINS]
Nabe.
Sir.
[AINS] Please exterminate Khajit
and his followers for me.
I'm going to take care
of this woman myself.
It will be done.
[AINS]
Keep an eye on the sky.
Lord.
[AINS]
Clementine.
Let's finish our business
over here if you don't mind.
Okay!
This girl is harmless.
"Cast Twin Maximize Magic"!
What?!
"Electrosphere"!
[KHAJIT cackles]
Impressive.
How annoying.
Why don't you just
roll over and die
like a good little rodent?
[CLEMENTINE humming]
I guess those men
I killed in town
were friends of yours,
is that right?
Did you come here to avenge them
or something stupid like that?
[giggles] Did you notice
the magic caster
was really a girl? She kept
insisting that someone
would come to rescue them.
But I got bored
of waiting around.
[AINS]
I barely knew those adventurers.
Really? That's disappointing.
I was so looking forward
to all the whining about
how they meant so much to you
and I had no right to kill them.
Please say you're
not going to have
one of those boring deaths.
I can't get hard
if you're not angry.
[AINS]
This isn't vengeance.
They were in your way and
needed to be dealt with.
I would have done the
same thing in your shoes.
It would be hypocritical
to condemn you.
That being said, by killing
them, you've robbed me
of valuable assets. They were
vital components in my plans.
In other words...
You're in my way!
[CLEMENTINE]
Fabulous.
I promise there's no
way you can defeat me
by yourself, though.
It's a shame you left your
spellcaster with Khaji.
He gets to kill her.
No fun for me.
[AINS] Nabe can take you out
just as easily as I can.
You're hilarious!
All it takes is a slice
and a quick stab.
I've killed plenty of
magic users that way.
[AINS]
Impressive.
I know all the
people strong enough
to fight me in this country.
There's a person from Blue Rose
and one from Drop of Red.
Then probably Gazef Stronoff.
And maybe Brain Unglaus.
[AINS]
Ha. Thanks for the information.
Sounds like you need
to be given a handicap.
Consider it a sympathetic
parting gift from me to you.
[growls] You must not
have a brain underneath
that helm of yours if you
think you can talk to me
like that and get away with it.
The inhuman Lady
Clementine doesn't
lose brawls to
nobodies like you.
You're about to learn
why people fear me!
[AINS]
I see nothing to be scared of.
You're a joke.
Now shut up and fight!
[AINS] I finally find the
person that I had been seeking.
She's hiding deep within
the heart of the cemetary.
The fool who destroyed
The Swords of Darkness,
some of my most valuable
assets thus far,
is a psychotic female
fighter named Clemintine.
She uses her
signature, "Stiletto,"
to torture and maim her prey,
and even claims her skills
have surpassed
human limitations.
Well... I'll have to show
her what it really means
to be inhuman.
Chapter nine:
"The Dark Warrior."