[SOLUTION] You call this a
meal?! It tastes like dog food!
My apologies, madam.
[SOLUTION]
Enough!
I do not wish to stay here
a moment longer, Sebas.
Understood, my lady.
[SOLUTION]
Hmph.
Zach!
Yes, Miss?
Stop stuffing your face
and get the carriage.
I want this town at my
back within the hour.
Please, return to your meals,
ladies and gentlemen.
[knocking]
Excuse me, Miss.
I'm afraid I took the
performance too far.
Please, forgive me.
There is no need to lower
your head to me, Solution.
I am supposed to be
your butler for as long
as we continue this charade.
Yes, that is true
for this mission.
However, as a member of
the Pleiades, I am your
subordinate first and
foremost, Master Sebas.
Well, Lady Shalltear has
most certainly grown anxious
to play her part in all of this.
I will let her know the
time has finally come.
By the way, is Zach
performing as we expected?
Yes, sir.
As we speak, he is meeting with
a filthy man in the back alley.
[ZACH]
She's perfect.
[SOLUTION]
They are planning to attack us
somewhere outside the city.
And use me for all manner
of unspeakable things.
I am happy to hear it.
Everything is unfolding exactly
as Lord Ains predicted.
One more thing, master.
I'd like to have that man
once he's no longer useful.
It would be best to ask
Lady Shalltear first,
but I'm sure it will be fine.
[SOLUTION]
Thank you very much.
And why are you
so interested in him?
[SOLUTION] He thinks he will
get to enjoy a piece of me.
So, I thought I'd
let him have a taste.
A little slice of heaven
before he sees hell.
[chuckles]
[SHALLTEAR]
Let me guess, Sebas.
Our unfortunate prey finally
took a bite of the bait?
[SEBAS]
Yes. Wonderfully.
[SHALLTEAR]
It's about time.
With any luck, we will find
a magic or martial arts user
that will suit Lord Ains, and
we will return to him soon.
If I may, my lady.
There is something
I've wanted to ask you
for some time now.
Go on.
[SEBAS] It's quite apparent
that you and Lady Aura
do not get along well.
I was wondering if there was
a special reason for that.
I always thought
we got along fine.
There is no bad blood
between the two of us.
I simply tease her
because my creator,
Lord Peroroncino,
decided that I should.
You see, that flat-chested
insect's creator,
Lady Bukubuku Chagama,
is actually the sister
of Lord Peroroncino.
I never knew about this!
I happened to overhear
my blessed creator
talking about it with
Lord Ains one evening.
[PERORONCINO groaning]
[MOMONGA]
Is something wrong, Peroroncino?
[PERORONCINO] My sister is
the lead voice in the new
H-Game I just bought.
[MOMONGA] Well, Bukubuku
Chagama is a popular
voice actor these days. But I
totally feel your pain, man.
[PERORONCINO] I was itchin'
to hit it hardcore, too.
[MOMONGA] Better save those
tissues for another day.
What is a "voice-actor"?
Apparently, voice actors have
an incredibly important job.
They imbue souls into beings
that are otherwise soulless.
To put it plainly,
they bring things to life,
like any decent god should.
I see.
Thank you for sharing all of
that with us, Lady Shalltear.
You honor us both.
Learning more about
the Supreme Beings
is truly humbling.
Especially from you, my lady.
--[HORSE whinnies]
--[knocking]
[MERCENARY 10A]
Knock-knock, girlie!
Why don't you come outside?
We wanna play with ya!
You'll let me have a
go afterwards, right?
I mean, I am the one
who brought them here.
[ZACH gasps]
[SHALLTEAR giggles]
This ain't your lucky
night, sweetheart.
Just go along with it and we
won't take your life, okay?
You got a hell of a
pair for a little girl.
As if I would let you defile
me with your dirty hands.
Oh god, what the hell
happened to my hand?
Humans make far too much racket.
[MERCENARIES gasp, whimper]
A magic caster!
This is already boring.
Do me a favor and
clean up the rest of them.
[MERCENARIES screaming]
But how? Who the hell
are these people?
[SOLUTION]
Mister Zach. This way.
[gasps]
[laughs]
[gulps]
[MERCENARYS screaming, groaning]
[screams]
[ZACH]
Stop it! Stop it! Oh, god!
Someone save me!
Please, have mercy!
[laughing]
[SHALLTEAR] It looks like
we've managed to do nothing
but waste our precious time.
[BRIDE 10A]
Lady Shalltear, we have found
the nest of these humans.
There is a man among
them, called Brain,
who is adept at
martial arts skills.
Apparently, he fought
on equal terms
with Gazef, the royal head
warrior of this kingdom.
I know that name.
I believe he's considered the
strongest fighter in Re-Estize.
This "Brain" sounds like
the perfect candidate.
Indeed, he does.
However, Solution and I must
part ways with you here,
as we have a mission
to collect information
in the capital for Lord Ains.
May we meet in the
Great Tomb of Nazarick.
[MERCENARIES screaming]
[BRAIN gasps]
Sounds like a party.
[MERCENARY 10F panting]
Huh?
Brain, thank the Gods!
We're being attacked!
Yeah, that much is
obvious. How many?
[MERCENARY 10F] Oh, right.
There are two of them.
Both women.
Women? Are you pulling my leg?
[MERCENARY 10F]
Uh--
[BRAIN]
I'll handle this one.
Head back. Fortify
our inner defense.
[MERCENARY 10H screams]
[gasps]
[screams]
A vampire, huh? Great.
This'll be fun. Very fun.
But you're all by yourself, sir.
If I were you, I would call
the rest of your friends,
then you might have a chance.
Don't need 'em.
Those morons would only
cramp my style, anyway.
[SHALLTEAR]
My, aren't you brave?
[growls]
[yelps]
No. It's my turn.
[BRAIN]
Hm...
My name is Brain Unglaus.
And, you are?
Oh! So that's what we're doing.
How utterly adorable.
My name is
Shalltear Bloodfallen.
I hope you will entertain me
well before you perish.
[BRAIN] She thinks she's
unbeatable. Typical monster.
[BRAIN] But she won't be faster
than my God Flash strike.
And she can't get past
my Perception Field.
Now...
I take it you've finished
with your preparations?
All right. Then let
the massacre begin.
[BRAIN]
Gazef.
I developed the God Flash and
Field so I could beat you.
[BRAIN] And if I combine
the two of them, I will.
"Blade Technique."
[BRAIN]
"Whistling Wind"!
[gasps]
[gasps] How? There's no way!
I think you just realized
how futile this is.
I may be a petite and
beautiful little monster,
but I'm also cold,
cruel, and ruthless.
If you have another attack,
you should try it now.
[gasps]
What's the matter?
Was that all of the
martial arts you know?
Martial arts? Is that what
you think I was doing?
[BRAIN yells]
[yells]
[SHALLTEAR yawns]
What's wrong?
Are you tired already?
I thought you'd have
more stamina than this.
Huh?
How strange.
I thought you used
martial arts to increase
your strength and speed.
[BRAIN gasps]
[SHALLTEAR] But I don't
notice any difference.
You're just as weak as you
were before we started.
If you want to make
a good impression,
you, sir, are going to have
to work a lot harder than that.
[BRAIN sobs]
There is still hope for you.
The fact that you know
martial arts means
you might be of minor use
to my beloved master.
I am such an idiot.
[yells]
[SHALLTEAR] Oh, my. Are we
playing a game of tag now?
You really like to
fool around, don't you?
Too bad.
[SHALLTEAR] I've wasted enough
time with you as it is.
[SHALLTEAR cackling]
Commander?
[BRAIN whimpering]
It's Brain!
[MERCENARY 10G gasps]
The hell?
That's strange.
[SHALLTEAR cackling]
[MERCENARY COMMANDER
10A gasping]
[SHALLTEAR]
Now that we're done with tag,
let's play hide and seek!
A vampire. Fire at will!
[SHALLTEAR grunts]
Now! Shoot her!
[SHALLTEAR growling]
[MERCENARY COMMANDER
10A groaning]
[MERCENARY 10G gasping]
[SHALLTEAR growls]
[MERCENARY 10G whimpering]
[gasping]
[screams]
[SHALLTEAR]
Time for the main dish!
A hole?
[SHALLTEAR roars]
He's escaped me!
[BRIDE 10A]
Lady Shalltear.
I'm sorry for intruding,
but there are humans
heading this way.
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
[SHALLTEAR]
Fortune smiles!
[MAGIC CASTER 10A]
As I thought! A vampire!
Imbue your blades with silver!
Don't look into her eyes!
We must fight to escape!
[SHALLTEAR]
I know I have to capture them.
But I want to kill them!
I want to rip them
limb from limb,
and bathe in their blood!
[ADVENTURERS gasp, groan]
[SHALLTEAR cackles]
[ADVENTURERS whimper]
[BRITTA whimpers]
[SHALLTEAR] My, aren't
you precious, sweetie?
I think I'll save
you for dessert.
[SHALLTEAR cackles]
[ADVENTURER 10D screams]
[MAGIC CASTER 10A gasps]
No...
[SHALLTEAR]
Come here, dessert.
My sweet tooth is calling.
Let me gobble you up!
[BRITTA whimpers]
[SHALLTEAR]
Huh?
[BRITTA grunts]
[BRITTA panting]
No, it can't be. This is...
Capture her! Bring
her to me alive!
[grunts]
Look in my eyes!
Where did you get this potion?
[BRITTA] A man clad in
black armor gave it to me
at one of the inns in E-Rantel.
Could she have been given orders
by the Supreme One? No.
He was probably
making connections.
What were you and your
party doing out here?
It was for a job.
We were hired to find a group
of soldiers turned mercenaries.
When we sensed that something
was off, we split up.
Split up? There are more?
Yes, ma'am.
We had a ranger
stationed further away,
in case we were ambushed
or the worst happened.
He's probably on his
way back to E-Rantel.
Then, the scream I heard was...
I'm such a fool! Come, children!
[SHALLTEAR] Find every last
human in this forest
and devour them!
[sobs] How could I let
this travesty happen
on my watch? Lord Ains will
reprimand me for sure.
My children were
defeated that easily?
[growls]
[SHALLTEAR]
That one is strong.
[SHALLTEAR growls]
Use it!
[SHALLTEAR]
You're in my way!
[SHALLTEAR yells]
[SLANE THEOCRACY CAPTAIN 10A]
Lady Kaire!
[ALBEDO]
I'm afraid I must report that
Shalltear Bloodfallen
has betrayed us.
[AINS]
"Master Source, Open." I see.
This is why you believe
Shalltear betrayed Nazarick?
After we lost contact with her,
I checked the Master
Source and discovered
this abnormality.
And the vampire brides
that accompanied her
have both perished.
[AINS] Is there a chance
Shalltear has died as well?
If that were the case,
her name would
disappear from the list.
Unfortunately, that
hasn't happened.
[MOMONGA]
She's got a point.
If we were still in Yggdrasil,
this status marker would
indicate that a third party
has used mind control magic
and temporarily turned
our NPC into an enemy.
But that should be impossible.
Since Shalltear is undead,
she has a passive skill
that nullifies all forms
of mind control instantly.
[AINS] From what we've
gathered, there are talents
and martial arts in this world
that did not exist in Yggdrasil.
Is it possible she has
fallen under the influence
of one of them?
[ALBEDO]
I do not know.
However, it does not change
the fact that she has revolted.
I suggest we send
a hunting party
to deal with her, immediately.
[AINS]
Hm...
[ALBEDO]
I will lead our forces.
Cocytus and Mare will accompany
me as vice-commanders.
We will need that much
to take Shalltear down.
Her strength is formidable.
[AINS] No. I feel that
would be too hasty.
First, we must confirm
whether she has revolted
of her own free will or not.
[MOMONGA] If something like
this can happen to the NPCs,
I need to find out what it
is and how to counter it.
Or Nazarick will crumble.
[AINS sighs]
If she betrayed us
because she is
displeased with me,
or our treatment of her,
I would understand.
Displeased?
If she truly thinks that after
you've been so merciful to us,
I won't allow her to live!
[AINS]
Please, Albedo, calm yourself.
Remember, my old
comrades created
all of your personalities.
They made you with
all of their hearts.
That includes the bad qualities,
as well as the good.
You are made exactly
as they wanted you.
And I love all of you for that.
--So, if Shalltear has indeed
--[ALBEDO] Loves? He loves us.
--betrayed me, she is simply
--following the path that
--So... He loves me!
--Peroroncino laid out for her.
Loves me. Loves me.
He loves me!
[AINS] Uh-- Hey, Albedo.
Weren't you listening?
I said "all of you."
Yes, I know.
But "all" includes me,
doesn't it?
Am I right, my lord, Ains?
[AINS]
I, w-well, yes, I suppose so.
--Lord Ains said he loves me!
--[AINS] Albedo, wait.
--That's not what I--
[ALBENDO] This is the
greatest day of my life!
[AINS] Anyway! Before
we do anything else,
we must find Shalltear.
[AINS]
An emergency announcement
has come from the
Adventurer's Guild.
According to the Guild Master,
a vampire in the form
of a young girl has appeared
not far from the capital.
In order to minimize
Shalltear's exposure,
I volunteer to hunt
her down myself.
Any embers that may fall upon
Nazarick must be destroyed.
Utterly... Completely...
Chapter 11: "Confusion
and Understanding."