( Drum beats )
¶
Tanjiro: I've been able
to survive this long.
I know I have what it takes!
Whether it's today or tomorrow,
I can assure you this!
( Kyogai growls )
Tanjiro: Without a shadow
of doubt in my mind,
I will not yield!
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( zenitsu and shoichi panting )
Zenitsu: Tanjiro,
where are you right now?
I can still hear
that creepy sound.
I just hope he's safe.
Shoichi: Um, zenitsu, is it me,
or are we just going
around and around in circles?
Zenitsu: I knew it! I was
getting the exact same feeling!
I knew I could rely on you
to help me out, shoichi!
All right.
Can you check to see
if this room is clear?
Hey, what's with that look?!
All right, all right, fine!
You win! I'll do it myself!
( Shuddering )
There's nobody here.
Let's go this way.
Where are you, tanjiro?
You can come out now!
- ( Drum beats )
- ( Rumbling )
( Both gasp )
Zenitsu: Wait.
Did this room just...
Flip over?!
( Gags )
( Both yelling )
¶
( drum beats twice )
( Rumbling )
( Woman vocalizing )
( Drum beating )
Tanjiro: I can do it.
I know I can.
I always finish what I start.
- ( Bones creak )
- ( Groans )
No matter what, even with
my body in this condition,
I can pull through
and keep fighting!
¶
show him that a few broken bones
isn't gonna slow me down!
( Grunting )
Damn it! I can't win like this.
I need more
than just determination.
Calm down. Use your head
to think things through.
( Drum beats )
Think, tanjiro! Think!
That was close.
I barely scraped by there.
Kyogai: Curses!
This is irritating.
I need to consume some marechi
before it's too late.
( Tanjiro grunts )
( Drum beats )
( Groans )
There's not even time to think!
( Drum beats )
Hey, you! What's your name?
Kyogai: Eh?
It's kyogai.
Tanjiro: Kyogai!
Listen, I'm not
giving you that child!
I won't bend to you!
It's futile!
( Kyogai growls )
Man: Don't you see
that it's futile?
Kyogai: I will
get my hands on that boy
and reclaim my rightful place
among the twelve kizuki!
( Drum beats )
¶
( growling )
( Drums beating )
Man: Don't you see
that it's futile?
This is so boring!
Disappointing. Your writing
is absolutely insipid.
Every last word on these pages
is utterly trite!
There's no beauty,
vulnerability, or impact.
Why don't you forget
this fantasy of being a writer?
It would simply be
a waste of ink and paper.
It doesn't help that you
never even step outside anymore.
It's no wonder
you're such a dull individual.
And, if that's the case,
you might as well stick
with your original hobby
of playing the drum.
Not that you're good enough
to be more than an amateur
with that, either.
( Kyogai gasps )
( Gasping )
( Growling )
( Drum beats )
( Growls )
Damn insect!
Get out of my sight!
Rapid drumming!
Tanjiro: Don't tell me he can
strike that drum even faster!
( Kyogai growls )
( Woman vocalizing )
( Growls )
( Tanjiro yelling )
The speed of these rotations
is making me dizzy! This is bad.
What a terrifying skill.
Not only that,
but now he's using
five claws instead of three!
Kyogai: Eh?
Tanjiro: I got it!
Now that I've dodged his strikes
without stepping
on those papers,
I can protect my wounds,
because I know
how to move around and breathe.
Take quick, shallow breaths.
Use that breathing technique
to reinforce the muscles
around your broken leg!
Also, right before
the claw attack,
there's a strong scent of mold.
( Sniffs )
I smell it! Here it comes!
¶
from above!
Left!
Right!
From behind!
Kyogai: Eh?
He's evading all of my attacks.
( Growls )
( Tanjiro breathes deeply )
Total concentration.
Water breathing.
¶
( Kyogai growls )
Tanjiro: Ninth form,
splashing water flow, turbulent!
Minimize the landing time
and area as much as possible.
Kyogai: He's adapting
to the changes of the room.
Tanjiro: Go, tanjiro.
Get within striking distance.
Closer. Don't give him
any room to breathe!
( Thread rings )
I see the opening thread.
Kyogai!
Your blood demon art
was truly incredible!
( Kyogai growls )
( Tanjiro groans )
( Kyogai groans )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Winces )
( Groans )
I took a deep breath
by mistake.
( Groans )
It's okay, tanjiro,
you can bear this. It'll pass!
Kyogai: Boy...
Tanjiro: Eh?
Kyogai: Answer me.
Did you really think...
My blood demon art...
Was incredible?
Tanjiro: I truly did.
However...
I can't forgive you
for killing.
Kyogai: I see.
Tanjiro: Oh, that's right.
Gotta get a blood sample.
Wow, it worked.
He said it would
automatically extract blood
when applied like this,
but seeing it in action
proves how crafty
yushiro really is.
- ( Cat meows )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
( Gasps ) A cat?
Oh! You're the one
who's going to deliver this
to miss tamayo, right?
Here we are. Good kitty!
You're all set!
All right. Take care!
( Cat meows )
Tanjiro: Oh.
I was told that,
under yushiro's spell,
it would be invisible
until it meowed,
and then vanish again
when it meowed a second time.
So it's true, then.
( Gasps ) Those kids.
I gotta find them!
Kyogai: My--my writing...
Man: Disappointing.
Your writing
is absolutely insipid.
Every last word on these pages
is utterly trite!
There's no beauty,
vulnerability, or impact.
¶
kyogai: It wasn't worthless.
At the very least,
that child didn't believe so.
He respectfully avoided
trampling upon my work.
Tanjiro: May your soul
rest in peace.
( Kyogai crying )
Both my blood demon art
and my drum playing...
Have been recognized.
Tanjiro: Kiyoshi! Teruko!
Are you here? Answer me!
Teruko! Kiyoshi!
( Teruko screams )
( Kiyoshi yells )
( Tanjiro groans )
Teruko: Uh...
Kiyoshi: Sorry, tanjiro.
Tanjiro: Why are the two of you
throwing stuff at me?
Kiyoshi: We're sorry
the drum we were using
disappeared, so we panicked.
Tanjiro: I see.
Well, you're safe. I'm glad.
( Teruko crying )
Tanjiro: You did a great job
hanging in there.
You, too, Kiyoshi.
Come on. Let's head outside.
Kiyoshi, hop on.
( Footsteps shuffling )
How's your leg feeling?
Kiyoshi: Not too bad.
Tanjiro: Just hang on
a little longer.
I'm picking up
zenitsu and shoichi's scent.
They're probably outside.
Seems they're both sa--
( gasps )
I smell blood.
Kiyoshi: What's the matter?
Nothing. Let's hurry along.
¶
- ( Thump )
- Swordsman: Take this!
Come on! Move it!
Now, you spineless coward!
Draw your sword, and face me!
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Shoichi sobbing )
Zenitsu: Tanjiro...
The box, I protected it.
You told me...
This was
more important to you...
Than your own life.
That's why I did it.
The fact is, I've always
had really good hearing.
There have been times
when I knew what people said,
even though
I had been fast asleep.
That really
creeped everyone out.
I don't hear any more demons.
You must have
finished the job, tanjiro.
I can hear you all
and also these
odd-sounding, loud footsteps.
Shoichi: Zenitsu! Zenitsu!
Please, wake up!
Oh. Thank goodness!
Are you all right?
( Zenitsu groans )
Shoichi: When the room
spun around earlier,
we ended up
getting thrown outside.
We fell
from the second-story window.
( Zenitsu gasps )
- Did we, really?
- Shoichi: Yeah
you made sure that I was
protected at the time, though,
so I didn't end up
getting hurt at all.
Zenitsu: I'm glad to hear that.
So what's
with all the tears, then?
Huh?
Now I understand!
I fell right onto my head,
didn't I?!
Shoichi: Yes.
Zenitsu: Am I gonna--
am I gonna die?!
Oh, no. The world
is starting to spin.
- Is this the end for me?!
- ( Swordsman laughing )
Zenitsu: What's going on?
I don't like that sound!
Kiyoshi: Watch out,
'cause, ready or not,
I'm comin' through!
( Zenitsu shrieks )
There it is again,
that terrifying boar monster!
( Swordsman laughs )
Picking up
a demonic presence here.
( Zenitsu gasps ) Hey, wait.
I know where I've heard
that voice before.
He's the fifth survivor.
During final selection,
he was the first
to rush up the mountain
and the first to come back down.
- What a force of nature!
- Swordsman: Hmm?
( Laughs )
I've found you, demon!
( Roars )
Zenitsu: Stop it!
¶
swordsman: What the hell?
Who are you?
Get outta my way!
Zenitsu: My name
is zenitsu agatsuma!
I'm a demon slayer,
the same as you!
Swordsman: Oh? Are you, now?
Then, you should already know!
We gotta get rid
of that thing at all costs!
Now get the hell out of my way!
Zenitsu: I refuse!
This belongs to tanjiro--
swordsman:
Don't you argue with me!
I'll deal with him and his box
if that's the case.
I won't say it again. Move!
( Zenitsu whimpering )
Swordsman: Do you wanna die?
Zenitsu: This box,
I won't let you touch it!
I don't know what's inside,
but I know that it's
precious to tanjiro!
Swordsman: Are you serious?
Use your damn head!
There's a demon in that box!
Don't you get that?
Zenitsu: Of course I do!
I've known that
from the very start!
I knew he was
traveling with a demon,
because the sounds demons make
aren't anything like a human.
That said,
the sounds I hear from tanjiro
are so kind and gentle,
it makes me want to cry.
I don't think I've ever heard
anything like it before.
All living creatures
constantly give off vibrations.
The world is full
of sounds ringing out...
Breathing, heartbeats,
the rhythm
of blood circulating.
By listening closely,
I'm able to tell
what kind of thoughts are
going through someone's head.
Even so, I've been deceived
by others many times.
That's because
I've always stubbornly believed
in whomever I wanted.
Tanjiro, despite being
a demon slayer,
is traveling with a demon,
but I'm sure he has
a good reason for doing so.
Whatever that reason may be,
I'm sure I can
put my faith behind it.
I'll do it.
Swordsman: Huh?
Zenitsu: I'll ask him.
I'll ask tanjiro
about the demon myself.
Until that happens,
just leave it alone!
( Both grunting )
Swordsman:
Let go of me, damn it!
- ( Zenitsu yelps )
- Swordsman: You're a pest!
( Grunts )
( Growls )
Zenitsu: I won't
let you touch that!
It's important to tanjiro.
Stay away from it!
You're not laying a finger on it
until he gets back!
Swordsman: Damn you!
( Sputters )
Take this!
- ( Blows landing )
- ( Both grunting )
Swordsman: Move it!
Zenitsu: No! I refuse!
¶
swordsman: Take this!
Come on! Move it!
Now, you spineless coward!
Draw your sword, and face me!
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Shoichi sobbing )
Zenitsu: Tanjiro...
The box, I protected it.
You told me...
This was
more important to you...
Than your own life.
That's why I did it.
Swordsman: You idiot!
After all that bluster,
you don't even bother
to draw your sword!
If you're a fellow demon slayer,
then let's see you fight!
( Zenitsu groaning )
( Tanjiro growls )
Swordsman: If you're
not gonna fight,
then get the hell out of my way!
¶
- ( blows landing )
- ( Both grunting )
Swordsman: Move aside!
- ( Blows landing )
- ( Both grunting )
( Tanjiro growls )
Swordsman: Fine, then.
If all you're gonna do
is keep me from doing my job,
then you leave no choice,
but to take you out
along with that box!
( Zenitsu groaning )
Tanjiro: Stop it!
Swordsman: Huh?
( Zenitsu groaning )
Tanjiro: I said stop!
( Yelling )
( Chorus vocalizing )
¶
( singing in Japanese )