¶
( Nezuko groans )
Shinazugawa:
Come on out, demon.
( Nezuko grunts )
Tanjiro: Stop it!
Shinazugawa: It's the human
blood you love so much!
( Nezuko shuddering )
( Singers vocalizing )
( Nezuko growling )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Nezuko gasping )
Shinazugawa:
What's the matter? Go on.
You know you want it.
( Nezuko gasping )
( Tanjiro grunting )
Shinobu: Iguro,
you're being too rough.
Ease up a bit, will you?
Iguro: I'm only doing this
because he's trying to escape.
Shinobu: Tanjiro, if you use
any breathing techniques
while your lungs are squeezed,
it'll force your veins to burst.
Uzui: His veins will burst?!
I like it! Sounds dramatic!
Come on! Show me!
( Mitsuri whimpers )
( Gyomei cries )
What a poor soul.
My heart goes out
to this unfortunate child.
Namu amida butsu.
( Nezuko growling )
( Shinazugawa chuckles )
( Tanjiro groaning )
Shinobu: Tanjiro!
( Iguro gasps )
( Tanjiro grunting )
Nezuko!
( Nezuko gasping )
¶
Tanjiro: She's my sister!
I was taking her to get help!
I don't know how it happened,
but Nezuko is different
from the others!
( Chopping vegetables )
( No audible dialogue )
( Birds chirping )
( Running footsteps )
Urokodaki: I convinced her
that all humans are her family.
I told her to protect them.
Nezuko: Humans are
to be protected and saved.
Never hurt them.
I will never hurt them.
( Gasping )
Hmph!
( Shinazugawa gasps )
( Tanjiro sighs )
( Nezuko gasping )
Ubuyashiki:
Tell me what happened.
Woman: The demon girl
turned her head away in disgust.
Woman 2: Despite Shinazugawa
stabbing her three times
and then flaunting his
bloody arm in front of her face,
she restrained herself
from biting him.
( Shinazugawa groans )
Ubuyashiki: There it is,
undeniable proof
that Nezuko won't attack humans.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Iguro grunts ) What do you
think you're doing, Tomioka?
Ubuyashiki: Tanjiro...
I'm sure that, even after this,
there are some
who can not accept Nezuko.
Work towards
changing their minds.
Prove to them
that you and Nezuko
can be helpful to our cause
by fighting as demon slayers.
( Tanjiro gasps )
What is this I'm feeling?
It's like I'm floating.
His voice...
Is it because of this man's
voice that my body feels light?
Ubuyashiki: Go out
and defeat a twelve kizuki.
Do that, and you
will be accepted by all.
Your words will carry
more weight as a result.
( Tanjiro gasps )
All right.
My sister and I...
Will defeat Kibutsuji!
Rest assured,
we will strike him down
and stop
this endless cycle of misery!
¶
Ubuyashiki: That is
a bit ambitious for you two.
Let's start by defeating
a twelve kizuki first.
( Tanjiro sputters )
Yes, sir.
( Mitsuri chuckles )
You mustn't laugh, Mitsuri.
- Keep it together.
- ( Shinobu laughing )
Ubuyashiki: It goes
without saying that the Hashira
of the Demon Slayer Corps
have phenomenal skills.
( Hashira chuckling )
Ubuyashiki:
They have trained themselves
to the brink of death
and have defeated it,
as well as those
of the twelve kizuki.
Rengoku: Yes! A noble pursuit!
Ubuyashiki: That is why
the Hashira receive respect
and favorable treatment,
so it would be best for you
to mind your manners
when addressing them, Tanjiro.
Tanjiro: Yes, sir.
Ubuyashiki: Also,
Sanemi, Obanai,
don't torment
the younger ones too much.
Iguro: As you wish.
( Nezuko grunts )
Shinazugawa: As you wish.
Ubuyashiki: We have concluded
our business with you, Tanjiro.
You may step back.
Shinobu: If that's
the case, master,
allow me to take Tanjiro
into my abode.
Tanjiro: Huh?
Shinobu: All right, then!
Take them away, please!
( Running footsteps )
- Nezuko: Hmm?
- ( Kakushi gasps )
Kakushi 2: Pardon me
for cutting in front!
( Tanjiro grunts )
( Footsteps receding )
Ubuyashiki: Now then, let us
begin the Hashira meeting.
Tanjiro: Hold on just a second,
if you would!
Both Kakushi: Come back here!
- ( Tanjiro grunts )
- ( Singers vocalizing )
Tanjiro: Please,
allow me to head-butt
that man covered in scars!
I need to do it!
Kakushi 2: Quiet!
Keep your mouth shut!
Tanjiro: One head-butt for
every time he stabbed Nezuko!
Show me where it says
you're not allowed
to head-butt
another Demon Slayer!
Kakushi 1: Be silent!
Settle down now!
- Tanjiro: Let go of me!
- Kakushi 2: Cut it out!
Muichiro: You're not allowed
to interrupt the master,
all right?
Kakushi 2: We beg your pardon!
Kakushi 1: Yes, yes!
Please forgive us!
- Master Tokito...
- Kakushi 2: We're very sorry!
Our sincerest apologies!
Mitsuri: Muichiro!
What a fine boy! So impressive!
Muichiro: Just leave now.
Both Kakushi: Yes, sir!
Ubuyashiki: Tanjiro...
Give Tamayo my regards.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Singers vocalizing )
Tanjiro: Hold on a second.
Did I just hear him
mention miss Tamayo?
Kakushi 1: Don't you
say another word!
We got scolded because of you!
Kakushi 2: I thought
I was gonna wet myself!
Kakushi 1: You don't know
how terrifying the Hashira are!
Kakushi 2: Try to read the room
next time!
Kakushi 1:
I will never forgive you!
Kakushi 2: Neither will I!
Kakushi 1: Apologize to us!
Kakushi 2: Yeah! Apologize!
Tanjiro: I-I'm sorry.
)
- Kakushi 1: Hello!
Anyone home?
Is there anyone here?
Is there any--( Groans )
Kakushi 2: No one's
coming to the door, huh?
Kakushi 1: Let's go
check out the yard.
( Kakushi 2 groans )
Hey, walk on your own two feet.
Tanjiro: Mm, sorry.
It's just my whole body's
aching up a storm.
And I thought
the headquarters were big,
but this mansion's
in a league of its own, huh?
Eh?
That's right.
Wasn't this place called
the butterfly mansion?
¶
Kakushi 2:
Well, would you look at that?
There is someone here.
Kakushi 1:
That would be, um...
Oh, right! The Tsuguko.
I believe her name is...
Tanjiro: A "Tsuguko"?
Kakushi 2: Lady Kanao Tsuyuri.
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
it's that girl
from final selection.
Kakushi 2: From what I was told,
she stomped you real good
last night.
You don't remember that?
A Tsuguko is a Swordsman
trained by a Hashira.
Only those with impressive skill
are chosen.
Don't let her
being a girl fool you.
Kakushi 1: Please forgive us,
lady Tsuyuri.
We were ordered to come here
by lady Kocho.
Permission to enter
the mansion, ma'am.
Uh, if that's all right?
You don't mind, do you?
- Woman: Who are all of you?!
- ( Kakushi shriek )
Kakushi 2:
We're here on behalf of...
Kakushi 1: Lady Kocho!
Woman: That boy
is injured, correct?
You're the Kakushi.
Please come this way.
Kakushi 1: Y-yes, ma'am!
Kakushi 2: She's fast.
( Tanjiro sighs )
Zenitsu: Five times?!
I gotta take this
five times a day?!
And I have to keep taking it
for three months?!
It's such
a horribly bitter taste, too!
I'm not gonna want
to eat a single thing
after taking that!
You're telling me
that my arms and legs
will be restored just by taking
this medicine?! Really?!
Girl: Would you
please stop shouting?
Zenitsu: Explain to me
how that's gonna work!
I don't understand at all!
Woman: Still making a fuss,
even now?
Zenitsu: ...Forget even
just one time?! Huh?! Huh?!
What'll happen
to my arms and legs?!
- Tanjiro: Zenitsu!
- Zenitsu: Tell me! Tell me!
Woman: Please lower your voice!
Zenitsu: Please! Please!
Woman: How many times
have we explained it to you now?
If you don't stop this,
we'll have to restrain you!
( Zenitsu babbling )
Woman: Oh, for goodness's sake!
Tanjiro: Zenitsu.
( Zenitsu shrieks )
Tanjiro: What happened?
Are you all right?
So you came up the mountain
after all.
Zenitsu: T-Tanjiro.
( Wails )
- It was terrible, Tanjiro...
- Kakushi 2: Uh...
Zenitsu: Just awful!
I got bit by this icky spider,
and it really hurt!
( Sniffs ) That girl's
been yelling at me
ever since I arrived
at this place also!
- I hate my life!
- Kakushi 2: Hey,
stop crying on me.
I've got nothing
to do with this.
Tanjiro: Zenitsu, did you...
Get smaller or something?
( Zenitsu gurgles)
I almost
got turned into a spider,
so my arms and legs
are really short right now.
Tanjiro:
So that's what happened.
And the others?
Where are Inosuke and murata?
Zenitsu: I don't know
about anyone named murata,
but Inosuke's right over there.
- Tanjiro: Oh, you're right!
- ( Singers vocalizing )
He's been here all this time,
and I didn't notice!
( Kakushi 2 groans )
( Tanjiro grunts )
Inosuke! I'm glad you're safe.
I'm so relieved. ( Gasps )
Sorry I couldn't rescue you.
( Inosuke hoarse ) It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Kakushi 2: Help! I need
a handkerchief or something!
- Tanjiro: Your voice.
- Kakushi 2: Ugh!
- Tanjiro: Is that really you?
- Kakushi 2: Get it off! Hey!
Is anybody listening to me?!
Zenitsu: I heard he mangled
his throat or something.
Tanjiro: Huh?
Zenitsu: I don't know
all the details,
but I heard
he got hit in the neck,
and when he yelled at the top
of his lungs sometime after,
that's what pushed him
over the edge.
It really messed him up,
as you can hear.
The whole thing has taken
the wind out of his sails
and made him really passive.
You know, it's kind of funny.
( Titters )
( Crazed laughter )
Tanjiro: Why are you cackling
all weird like that suddenly?
What's going on?
Zenitsu: Eh?
Inosuke: I'm sorry...
For being so weak.
- ( Tanjiro sighs )
- Kakushi 2: Eww.
Tanjiro: Don't be sad, Inosuke.
This isn't like you at all.
Zenitsu: Yeah,
there's nothing to worry about!
You did great!
Tanjiro: I'm just so happy
that you're all right!
( Zenitsu shrieks ) Wait!
Did I take
my morning medicine?!
Did you see me take it?!
Did anybody see me take it?!
Anyone?!
( Inosuke snoring )
Tanjiro: Zenitsu, Inosuke...
You're alive. I'm so glad.
( Footsteps shuffling )
( Curtains rustling )
It's all right now.
They said it was fine for you
to use this room, Nezuko.
( Groans ) Ouch, ouch, ouch.
That whole encounter up on
the mountain was really brutal.
I gotta be honest.
Everything hurts right now.
( Nezuko sighs )
Tanjiro: Nezuko...
What you did,
protecting me on the mountain,
thank you.
There are the others, too,
Tomioka, Urokodaki.
They've all gone out and risked
their lives on our behalf.
It's really something, huh?
I-I have to become stronger.
Take today.
If it weren't
for the Hashira's master,
we may not have been spared.
( No audible dialogue )
Tanjiro: That man's voice...
It was mysteriously soothing.
Just listening to him speak
made my body feel light.
Who is he, exactly?
( Gasps )
( Nezuko breathing softly )
Tanjiro: That makes sense.
You've had a long day.
Even though
I'm in a lot of pain right now,
I have to keep pushing forward.
That's because
I'll be a grown man one day,
and then I'll become old
and pass on.
After that,
if you're still a demon,
then you'll be lonely.
That would be far too lonely,
wouldn't it?
( Nezuko breathing softly )
Tanjiro: I promise...
I will turn you
back into a human.
¶
( singers vocalizing )
Ubuyashiki: Just as
you all have reported,
the carnage of the demons
has grown more than ever,
meaning the threat to human life
in turn is greater
than it has ever been.
We must bolster the ranks
of the demon slayers.
What, then, are your thoughts?
Shinazugawa: The incident
on mount natagumo says it all.
The caliber of demon slayers
has dropped tremendously.
Most of them are useless.
The trainers must have
gone blind or something.
You'd think
they could at least tell
if someone's competent or not.
Uzui: Well, that kid today
sure packed a lot of power.
He landed
that dazzling blow on you.
He's got potential.
( Shinazugawa scoffs )
Shinobu: The more
the human race grows,
the harder it becomes
to control and unify them,
and in this era, that seems
to be even more true.
Gyomei: There are those
who've joined us
after their loved ones
were slaughtered,
and there are those
of noted pedigree
who have hunted demons
for generations,
but for everyone else,
it's another matter.
Asking laymen for the same
or even greater commitment
to our cause, I feel,
would be much too cruel.
Rengoku:
But consider that this boy
soon after joining
encountered a twelve kizuki.
I think he can draw them out!
Even we rarely
get the chance to confront one!
I am envious!
Ubuyashiki: A fair point.
However, the fact
that lower-five demon
made such a drastic move
likely means Kibutsuji
is far from mount natagumo.
Like with asakusa,
whenever he wishes
to hide something,
he proceeds to create
a clever diversion
to throw us off his trail.
To be honest,
it's quite frustrating.
But as long as those demons
linger as they do now,
freely devouring humans and
gaining strength as a result,
there is only one thing
for us to do
for the sake
of those who have died.
I feel...
You who are present today,
the core Hashira,
are the finest unit
I have assembled
since the first breathing
swordsmen of the feudal era.
Tengen Uzui.
Kyojuro Rengoku.
Shinobu Kocho.
Mitsuri Kanroji.
Muichiro Tokito.
Gyomei Himejima.
Sanemi Shinazugawa.
Iguro Obanai.
Giyu Tomioka.
My beloved children...
I look forward
to seeing your success.
¶
Muzan Kibutsuji,
I swear that I shall defeat you.
We will bring you down
without fail.
¶
( singing in Japanese )