( Demons hissing,
grinding teeth )
¶
- ( Demon grunts )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
( Demon babbles )
( Nezuko growling )
( Singers vocalizing )
¶
( Nezuko growls )
( Yells )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Nezuko gasps )
( Grunts )
( Demon 2 chuckles )
Tanjiro: Nezuko!
( Nezuko grunts )
Tanjiro: No, don't chase him!
Get back here!
Come to me.
No, nezuko!
( Demon 1 growls )
( Growls )
Tanjiro: This is what
urokodaki was talking about.
Nezuko's a demon now.
She's not a weakling.
She doesn't need me
to protect her.
She can handle herself.
So maybe she can handle this.
If she can protect these two,
I can focus on my attack.
( Gasps )
( Nezuko growls )
Tanjiro: Nezuko!
( Flowing )
Nezuko, I'm going underground!
Keep them safe for me.
Can you do that?
( Nezuko grunts )
( Demon 1 laughs )
¶
Tanjiro: It's a swamp.
What are those?
It's clothing and stuff
that belonged to the people
who were taken.
So many innocent victims,
all murdered.
It's unforgivable.
Unforgivable!
( Demon 2 laughs )
Getting hard to breathe yet?
There isn't a whole lot of air
down here in the swamp.
Also, the darkness
closing in on you
only adds
to the weight you feel.
( Laughs )
- ( Demon 3 hissing )
- Demon 2: You can't move
the way you would aboveground
down here.
You should've looked before
you leapt, you stupid fool!
( Demon 3 hissing )
( Grinding teeth )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Demons hissing,
grinding teeth )
Tanjiro: You underestimate me.
After all, where do you
think I got my training?
( Panting )
The air's even thinner
up on mount sagiri
than it is down here!
( Singers vocalizing )
Besides...
Some moves only unleash
their full potential underwater!
( Gasps )
( Demon 3 hisses )
Tanjiro: Guess it
goes both ways.
They move even faster here!
But it doesn't matter.
All I have to do is slash
when they get close enough.
I'll use the form that works
even when I don't have
sure footing.
A quick and violent twist
of my entire body,
generating a powerful vortex!
( Demon 2 growls )
( Demon 3 hisses )
Tanjiro: I've got the scent,
the opening thread!
Total concentration!
Water breathing!
Sixth form!
Whirlpool!
( Gasps )
( Gags )
Can't breathe.
I gotta get out of here!
Hurry!
( Flowing )
( Kazumi gasps )
( Demon hisses )
( Both grunting )
( Demon gags )
This girl's powerful!
Seems like she hasn't
picked up any skills yet,
but she's still so strong.
He must have given her
a massive amount of blood.
( Grunts )
( Nezuko grunts )
Demon: She's so fast, I can't
get back down to the swamp.
At least I'm starting to pick up
the pattern
in all her one-note attacks.
( Groans )
It doesn't matter
if she can kick my head off
or if my organs explode.
Demons can regenerate
in no time!
( Chuckles )
( Kazumi gasps )
( Nezuko gasping )
Demon: That's right.
Now I'm gonna drill a hole
right through your face!
( Gasps )
( Screams )
Tanjiro: Hands off my sister!
¶
Demon: H-he just took me out?
This stupid kid
beat two of me already?!
( Whimpers )
( Nezuko grunts )
Tanjiro: You smell horrible.
You give off a scent
like rotten oil.
I know where it comes from.
Tell me, how many people
have you killed?
Demon: Give me a break already!
If women live too long,
they turn ugly,
and then they
won't taste good anymore!
I killed 'em for their own good!
( Tanjiro gasps )
Demon: You know,
you should be thanking u--
( gagging )
Tanjiro: Never mind.
Demon: Huh?
( Raspy breathing )
Tanjiro: What do you know
about muzan kibutsuji? Tell me!
( Demon gasping )
( Whimpering )
Tanjiro: Talk to me!
Come on! Talk!
Demon: I-I can't.
I-I can't tell you.
( Sobbing )
Demon: I can't do it.
I just can't.
Kibutsuji:
You mustn't tell a soul.
No one can know
anything about me.
Do you understand?
Don't forget.
I'm always watching you,
so if you tell anyone,
I will know about it.
Demon: I can't say! I can't!
I can't! I can't!
I can't! ( Sobs )
Tanjiro: Now the only thing
I smell is fear.
He's terrified!
Demon: I can't tell you,
all right?!
( Yells )
( Gags )
( Flesh crackling )
Tanjiro: I failed
to get any information again.
( Gasps ) Nezuko!
She's asleep,
and the bleeding stopped.
So that does help her recover.
I failed. I'm sorry.
But just hang on.
I promise you this,
I will make you human again.
( Kazumi shuddering )
Tanjiro: Mr. Kazumi...
Are you all right?
Kazumi: I lost my fiancﾉe.
How could I be all right?
Tanjiro: Mr. Kazumi...
You have to go on,
no matter what,
in spite of losing people...
Even though it's devastating.
( Kazumi growls )
How am I supposed to do that?!
You're just a kid!
What do you know?!
¶
( gasps )
Tanjiro: I'll be on my way now.
Here.
Hopefully you'll find something
of miss satoko's in there.
( Kazumi weeping )
( Gasps )
You've been through this
yourself, haven't you?
( Singers vocalizing )
I-I'm sorry!
I shouldn't have said that!
Please forgive me!
I'm so sorry!
His hands are heartbreaking,
hardened and thick
from training.
They're not the hands of a boy.
Tanjiro: I'm leaving
the girl with you.
Get her home safe!
Kazumi: I'll do that!
I promise.
( Crow caws)
( Singers vocalizing )
Tanjiro: I'm not alone.
How many people have you killed?
Tortured? Tormented?
I'll never forgive you,
muzan kibutsuji.
I'll make you pay.
( Crow caws )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Crow: Head to Asakusa,
Tokyo now!
Rumor has it
a demon's lurking around there!
Caw!
( Tanjiro gasps )
I've got
another mission already?
Crow: Oh, yes, you do!
Tanjiro: Could you
at least give me a minute?
Crow: No time. Move it!
Tanjiro: Come on.
Just give me a chance to--
crow: Just shut up,
and get a move on!
Tanjiro: Hey, knock it off!
¶
( overlapping chatter )
The big cities have come
a lot further than I expected.
It's nighttime,
but it's so bright out.
The buildings are so tall!
What's the deal?!
Incredible and overwhelming.
( Trolley horn beeps )
( Tanjiro gasps )
This is making me dizzy.
Uh, let's go this way.
- ( Woman moaning )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
So sorry to bother you.
¶
( singers vocalizing )
( Dog barking )
- Pardon me, sir.
- Shopkeeper: Huh?
Tanjiro: Could I get
a bowl of udon with grated yam?
Shopkeeper: Why, yes.
Coming right up.
- ( Water bubbling )
- ( Chopping )
Tanjiro: I've never been
to a place like this before.
It's way too crowded.
( Nezuko sighing )
Shopkeeper:
Here's your udon with yam.
Let me know how you like it.
Tanjiro: Oh,
thank you very much.
( Wind blows )
¶
( bowl shatters )
( Tanjiro gasping )
( Sniffing )
( Gasps )
That scent!
Why is it here, and why now?!
It's the same scent
I found at my house!
( Crowd gasping )
Tanjiro: Muzan kibutsuji.
¶
it must be him! He's here!
Kibutsuji: Huh?
Tanjiro: I found him.
Girl: Daddy?
( Tanjiro gasps )
Girl: Who's that?
( Tanjiro gasps ) He's...
Kibutsuji: Don't worry, sweetie.
Tanjiro: What is this?
- Kibutsuji: Everything's fine.
- Tanjiro: Is he--
he's living here,
posing as a human!
Kibutsuji: I'm sorry. Is there
something I can do for you?
Are you all right?
You seem to be a bit flustered.
Woman: Darling,
what's the matter?
Girl: Don't worry, mother.
( Tanjiro gasping )
They're human.
The girl and the woman,
their scent is human.
But how?
Can't you tell?
This guy is a demon.
He eats people!
Woman: Who is this boy?
Kibutsuji: I really don't know.
I'm just as confused as you are.
I've never seen him before.
He must have made a mistake,
thought that I was someone else.
Woman: Oh, you think that's it?
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Man gasping )
Woman 2: Oh?
What's going on?
Are you all right, sweetheart?
( Man groaning )
( Gurgling )
Woman 2: You look pale.
( Demon roars )
Tanjiro: No! Stop!
( Demon growling )
( Woman 2 screaming )
- ( Crowd murmuring )
- ( Screaming continues )
¶
( singing in Japanese )