( Birds chirping )
Kakushi: Wake up.
I said wake up!
You gotta--
hey, can you even hear me?
Come on! Get up!
Are you gonna sleep all day?
Wake the hell up, will you?!
( Tanjiro gasps )
Hashira: I heard
he was a Demon Slayer
with a demon in tow,
so I was expecting
someone with more flair.
But it's just some
ordinary-looking kid? Too bad.
( Beads rattle )
Hashira 2:
We must see that this boy
is put on trial to be judged.
So it shall be!
Hashira 3: To think that he's
been protecting his sister,
who's now a demon.
What a brave and beautiful
display of sibling love!
Tanjiro: What--
who are these people--
Kakushi: Don't open your mouth
until you're told!
Do you know who you're
in the presence of?
These are the Hashira!
( Singers vocalizing )
Tanjiro: The Hashira?
What is that?
I have no idea.
Who are all these people?
Where even am I?
Shinobu: This is the demon
slayers's headquarters.
You are here because you,
Tanjiro kamado,
are to be put on trial.
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( birds chirping )
Shinobu: Before we
begin the trial,
why don't you explain the crime
you have been accused of--
Hashira 2:
There's no need for a trial!
Shinobu: Huh?
Rengoku: Protecting a demon
is a clear violation!
We can deal with this
on our own!
We shall execute them both!
Uzui: In that case,
I'll decapitate them with style.
I'll show you the most dramatic
spray of blood ever!
It'll be a spectacle.
Mitsuri: No way!
You'd really kill
such an adorable child as him?
Such a thought
fills my heart with sorrow.
Gyomei: Alas, to see
such a pitiful creature as this.
I grieve for him.
Perhaps it would have been
better if he hadn't been born.
Muichiro: Um, what was
the shape of that cloud again?
What was it called?
Tanjiro: Wait.
Where's Nezuko?
Kakushi: Hey, you.
The Hashira are speaking.
What are you looking at?
Your eyes should be over there.
These are the nine
highest-ranking swordsmen
in the Demon Slayer Corps.
Tanjiro: That's the Hashira?
Gyomei: Let's end his misery.
Rengoku: Right!
Uzui: And let's
do so with flair.
( Tanjiro grunts )
Kakushi: Hey!
Tanjiro: Nezuko!
Where did you take her?
Nezuko! Zenitsu!
Inosuke! Murata!
Hashira 4: Never mind this boy.
What will we do with Tomioka?
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
Hashira 4:
Seeing him standing there
without any restraints
is making me feel ill.
Based on what kocho told us,
he's just as guilty
of breaking the Corps rules.
How should we make him
take responsibility?
What kind of lesson
shall we teach him?
What do you have to say
for yourself, Tomioka?
Tanjiro: He's in this situation
because of me.
Mitsuri: Iguro, you're
as sharp tongued as ever, I see.
I love that side of you!
Tomioka's all by himself,
all stoic-like.
What a cutie!
( Water splashes )
Shinobu: Oh, I think it's fine.
He did come here
without resisting.
Let's come up
with a penalty later.
What I'm more interested in
is hearing this boy's story.
He's been traveling
with a demon alongside him,
despite being
a Demon Slayer himself.
I wish to hear why
and hear it straight
from the boy's mouth.
What he's done is unquestionably
against
the Demon Slayer Corps rules.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Shinobu: You are aware of that,
aren't you?
( Tanjiro stammers )
Shinobu: Tanjiro kamado,
why are you traveling
with a demon,
as a fellow Demon Slayer?
Uzui: Who cares why?
Shinobu: You can take your time.
Just answer the question.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Grunts )
- She's my--
she's my young--
( coughs )
( Groans )
Shinobu: It looks like
you need some water.
I can tell
you've injured your jaw,
so please drink slowly.
I added an anesthetic
to the water to help.
( Tanjiro panting )
Shinobu: Your wounds
are still healing,
so you shouldn't
push yourself too much.
Are you ready to tell us
your story, Tanjiro?
( Tanjiro panting )
That demon is my little sister!
My family was attacked
by a demon while I was gone,
and I lost almost everyone!
My sister
was turned into a demon,
but she's never hurt anyone!
She never has and never will!
She'll never harm a human being,
no matter what!
Iguro: Enough.
Spare us these absurd ramblings.
If she's family, it's no wonder
you're defending her.
I can't trust
a single word you're spouting.
I don't believe you
for a moment.
Gyomei: So sad.
He's been possessed by a demon.
Let us end this child's life
and free him
from this cursed existence!
Tanjiro: Please listen to me!
I became a swordsman in hopes
of finding a cure for her!
It has been two whole years
since Nezuko became a demon!
She's never devoured anyone
in that time!
Uzui: Your storytelling
is lacking
any vibrant sparks of color.
"She hasn't devoured anyone,
and she's not going to."
If you're gonna plead your case,
at least spice it up a bit!
( Bird trilling )
Muichiro: What's that bird
called again?
Was it...
Mitsuri: Excuse me.
Something about this
concerns me.
I find it hard to believe
the Master would have been
unaware of this situation.
( Men grunt )
Mitsuri: I don't think we should
act without his permission.
( Men grunt )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Mitsuri: Maybe it's best
if we wait until he arrives.
Tanjiro: My sister!
Let my sister fight by my side!
I know she can fight
as a Demon Slayer
to protect humans, so please...
Hashira 5: Well, well,
what kind of fun
do we have brewing here?
Is that the moron who brought
a demon along with him?
( Tanjiro gasps )
Hashira 5:
What the hell do you think
you're trying
to pull here, exactly?
Mitsuri: Those new scars
make Shinazugawa
look even more handsome!
Kakushi 2:
Please, Master Shinazugawa!
I must ask you
to put down that box.
Mitsuri: Wow!
Even when she's angry,
Shinobu still looks
as cool as ever.
Shinobu: Shinazugawa,
please don't act out of line.
Shinazugawa: Run that
by me again, kid?
"She can fight as a Demon Slayer
to protect humans."
Was that it?
You know what we call that?
Completely impossible,
you idiot!
( Nezuko gags )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Anyone who harms my sister
answers to me!
I don't give a damn
if you're one of the Hashira!
( Shinazugawa chuckles )
Well, how very nice for you.
( Tanjiro yelling )
Tomioka: Cease this!
The Master will be
arriving shortly!
( Shinazugawa gasps )
( Singers vocalizing )
( Mitsuri gasps )
( Shinazugawa gasps )
( Groans )
( Mitsuri chuckles )
Pardon me.
Shinazugawa: Damn you.
Iguro: Tomioka's outburst
must have been a distraction,
but that boy
still managed to get a blow in.
If you can't tell the difference
between good demons
and bad ones,
then you shouldn't be a Hashira!
Shinazugawa:
You no-good, little...
I'll destroy you!
( Tanjiro gasping )
Women: The Master
of the mansion has returned.
( Shinobu gasps )
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
Lord: My beloved children...
( Tanjiro gasps )
Lord: I thank you
for coming here this day.
Eturned.
Lord: Mmm.
Good morning to you all.
The weather
is strikingly nice today.
Perhaps with a blue sky?
Finding ourselves here
at the semiannual gathering
with all the same faces,
it brings me joy.
Tanjiro: So this is the Master?
He looks wounded.
No, sick, maybe.
( Gasps )
So quick!
I couldn't even react!
What is he--
( gasps )
¶
Shinazugawa: I am pleased
to see you in good health
as well, Master.
I fervently pray
for your continued good fortune.
Lord: I thank you, sanemi.
Mitsuri: Ohh!
I wanted to be the one
to welcome the Master!
Shinazugawa: If I may, Master,
before we start this meeting,
would you kindly enlighten us
about this young swordsman
right here,
who it would appear
has been accompanied by a demon?
Tanjiro: He didn't seem to have
any social graces before,
but now he's
speaking so formally.
Lord: But of course.
I apologize for any confusion.
Tanjiro and Nezuko
have both been sanctioned.
I would appreciate it if you'd
all accept this condition.
( Beads rattle )
Gyomei: Master, even though
it is something
you have requested,
I cannot bring myself to do it.
Uzui: I am also opposed to this!
A slayer traveling with a demon
is unacceptable!
Mitsuri: As for myself,
I shall do whatever it is
you wish, Master!
Muichiro: I'll forget, anyway,
so I'm fine either way.
Iguro: I won't trust them.
Absolutely not.
First of all, I loathe demons.
Rengoku: Although I respect you
with all my heart, Master,
I cannot abide by this!
I'm fully against it!
Shinazugawa: The Corps's mission
is to annihilate demons.
I ask that you punish
kamado and Tomioka!
Lord: The letter.
Woman: Yes, sir.
A former Hashira, Mr. Urokodaki,
sent along to us this letter
with a request.
I shall read to you
an abridged version.
"I ask you to allow Tanjiro
"and his sister
to accompany each other.
Because of her resilient
mental fortitude..."
Urokodaki: ...Nezuko has
not lost her human reason.
Even when starved,
she has never devoured a human,
and that is true
more than two years later.
Although the situation
sounds outlandish,
it is in fact reality.
In the event
that Nezuko does assault
another human being,
myself, as well as...
Woman: "...Tanjiro kamado
and giyu Tomioka,
will atone
by committing seppuku."
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Crying )
Shinazugawa: Who cares how they
choose to end their lives?
Fire, hanging,
it's all the same!
It doesn't guarantee
our safety!
Rengoku: Shinazugawa is right!
If she kills a human,
we can't turn back the clock.
That person
will be lost forever!
Lord: You do have a point.
Shinazugawa: So, then...
Rengoku:
What do you wish, Master?
Lord: We can't guarantee
that she won't attack humans.
We can't prove it.
That said...
We also cannot be certain
she will attack humans.
( Shinazugawa gasps )
Lord: Here is what we do know
about her for certain.
She has been abstinent
for over two years,
and there are three people
who would vouch for her
with their lives.
If this evidence is rejected,
one must offer in turn
an even more convincing
argument.
( Shinazugawa sputters )
Lord: Are any of you
able to do so?
( Rengoku grunts )
Lord: Also,
there is another thing
I'd like to relay to you,
my children.
Tanjiro has met kibutsuji
face to face.
( Hashira gasp )
Uzui: That's impossible!
Not even a Hashira
has ever crossed paths with him!
- ( Mitsuri yelps )
- Uzui: Did you, really?
What did he look like?
What are his powers?
Where did you see him?
Muichiro: Did you fight?
Shinazugawa:
What was kibutsuji doing?!
Did you find his stronghold?!
Answer me!
Uzui: Shut up!
I asked him first!
Come on. Tell us
what powers kibutsuji has!
( Singers vocalize )
( Silence )
¶
Lord: Speaking of that man,
we know he has
sent pursuers after Tanjiro.
While his goal may simply be
to silence Tanjiro,
now that he has
finally revealed himself,
I wish to seize
on this opportunity.
I also believe something
is happening to Nezuko
that kibutsuji never saw coming.
( Tanjiro sighs )
Lord: Do you agree with me now?
Shinazugawa:
I'm afraid I don't, Master.
If it were human, there would
be no question we'd spare it,
but after all
we've gone through,
after losing
countless of our brethren,
asking us to house a demon,
it's unacceptable.
( Lord grunts )
( Shinazugawa grunts )
Mitsuri: Huh?
Wh-what is he doing?
What is he doing?
Not all over the garden!
Shinazugawa: Hear me, Master!
The depravity of a demon,
I will prove it to you,
here and now!
Lord: Sanemi.
Shinazugawa: Hey, demon,
it's time for your dinner.
Take a bite.
- ( Blood dripping )
- ( Tanjiro groaning )
( Nezuko grunting )
( Wood scraping )
Shinazugawa:
No need to hold back.
Just show us your true colors,
and then I'll destroy you
right here.
Tanjiro: Get away from her!
Iguro: It's the daytime.
No good doing this now.
It'll only show itself
in the shadows.
Shinazugawa:
Master, please forgive
the discourtesy
I am about to commit.
¶
( Nezuko gasps )
Tanjiro: Stop it!
( Groans )
Shinazugawa:
Come on out, demon.
( Nezuko grunts )
Shinazugawa:
It's the human blood
you love so much!
Tanjiro: I can't breathe.
I can't move.
( Shinazugawa grunts )
- ( Nezuko shuddering )
- ( Singers vocalizing )
Tanjiro: N-Nezuko.
( Nezuko growling )
¶
( singing in Japanese )