Inosuke: Take this!
Come on! Move it!
Now, you spineless coward!
Draw your sword, and face me!
( Tanjiro gasping )
- ( Blows landing )
- ( Both grunting )
( Zenitsu groans )
Inosuke: Fine, then.
You leave no choice,
but to take you out
along with that box!
( Zenitsu groans )
Tanjiro: Stop it!
I said stop!
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Tanjiro: Get away!
Inosuke: Hmm?
( Tanjiro yells )
( Inosuke gags )
Zenitsu: I heard it!
He broke his ribs!
Tanjiro: Aren't you part
of the demon slayer corps?!
You must understand why Zenitsu
refuses to draw his sword,
because it's taboo for us
to fight each other
without provocation!
But here you are, giving him
a completely one-sided beating.
Is that fun for you?
You are the lowest of the low!
( Inosuke coughs )
( Laughing and coughing )
So that's how you feel?
I didn't realize.
In that case,
let's fight barehanded.
Tanjiro: No! Did you even
hear a word I just said?
Listen.
( Inosuke growls )
Tanjiro: We're not supposed
to fight each other in any way!
Using your hands
doesn't change things!
Are you listening to me?
- ( Inosuke growling )
- ( Tanjiro yelling )
( Gasps )
( Inosuke grunts )
Zenitsu: Man, look at this guy.
How is he able
to move like that?
And with some
of his ribs broken, no less.
( Inosuke growling )
- ( Grunts )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Zenitsu: If we're
being fair here,
Tanjiro's guilty of going
against the rules as well.
He broke his bones.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Inosuke snarls )
Tanjiro: The attacks
he's using...
( Inosuke grunting )
Tanjiro: They're unusually low.
The way we're fighting,
it's almost like...
I'm battling
a fearsome, four-legged beast!
Get down, and go
for a low blow of your own.
He won't be able to dodge this!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Tanjiro groans )
How is he this flexible?!
It doesn't even seem human!
Inosuke: What did you
think of that move?
Pretty damn amazing,
don't you think?
Zenitsu: Singing
his own praises like that?
Give me a break.
Inosuke: Let me demonstrate
what else I'm capable of.
( Laughing )
Tanjiro: Stop it!
What are you doing?
Performing a stunt like that
in your condition
won't be good for you!
Inosuke: So? What do I care?!
Nothing can take away
from this moment
and the pleasure I feel!
Tanjiro: But you have to think
about the future as well!
Inosuke: Why should I?
Eh?
Tanjiro: Now calm down!
Do you hear?!
( Zenitsu wails ) That sound!
Did both of your skulls
get fractured?!
( Inosuke gasping )
( Tanjiro stammers )
Zenitsu: Uh...
Huh?! Are you kidding me!
That's what you look like?!
Inosuke: What the hell
are you saying?
You got a problem
with my face or something?
Zenitsu: I don't know
what to make of you right now.
You've got this ripped body,
but such a delicate face
to go with it.
Inosuke: What?
Why are you obsessed
with my face all of a sudden?
Zenitsu: No! I-I'm not!
It was just an observation!
Children: Uh...
Tanjiro: There's nothing wrong
with your face.
In fact, the girlish shape,
size, and complexion
are quite attractive!
Inosuke: You're a dead man!
You wanna go?
Tanjiro: I don't!
I won't fight you anymore.
Inosuke: Come on. Head-butt me!
Tanjiro: No! I'm done!
Inosuke: I said do it!
Tanjiro: You're too worked up.
Why don't you just sit down?
Inosuke: I got a better idea!
How about I tell you my name?
It's Inosuke hashibira.
Don't you forget it!
Tanjiro:
How is that spelled, exactly?
Inosuke: Huh? I..
I don't know how
to read and write, okay?
All I know is that name
was written on my--
( gags )
Zenitsu: Huh? What's wrong?
Shoichi: Guess he froze.
( Inosuke stammering )
Tanjiro: What's the matter?
( Groans )
( Gurgling )
Zenitsu: Oh, no! He collapsed!
Is he dead?
Tanjiro: No, he's not.
I think it's a concussion.
I did head-butt him
really hard, though.
Teruko: But are you
all right, Tanjiro?
- Tanjiro: Yeah.
- Teruko: Amazing!
Can I touch your head?
Tanjiro: Sure.
Zenitsu: That's insane.
There's not a single drop
of blood from Tanjiro's head.
- How hard could it possibly be?
- ( Inosuke gurgling )
Zenitsu: I mean,
look at what it did to him.
Teruko: Tanjiro,
your head is so hard!
Tanjiro: You think so?
( Wind blowing )
( Birds chirping )
( Inosuke groans )
¶
( yelling )
( Zenitsu screams ) He's awake!
Inosuke: Fight me! Fight me now!
Get back here, you!
Zenitsu: I can't believe
this is how he acts
right when he wakes up!
( Squeals )
( Teruko yelps )
( Inosuke growls ) Huh?
What are you up to? Tell me!
( Rocks clatter )
Tanjiro: We're having a burial.
Inosuke: Burial?
Tanjiro: Yes,
and you should help out, too.
The fact of the matter
is lives were lost in there.
What's the point
in putting things
that have died
into the ground like that?
I'm not doing that,
not on your life!
Forget that crap!
Let's finish our fight!
Zenitsu: This guy's cold.
Did he really just ask
what the point
in burying people was?
¶
Tanjiro: I understand.
You can't do it,
because you're in too much pain.
Inosuke: Huh?
Zenitsu: I thought
it was just the boar guy,
but they're both crazy.
Tanjiro: Hey, it's all right.
Everyone handles
their pain threshold
differently, you know.
Moving those who died
outside the mansion
and then digging graves
for their bodies
is extremely hard work.
Zenitsu, these kids, and I
will do our best,
so don't you worry!
Kiyoshi: He's so odd.
- Shoichi: Strange guy.
- ( Inosuke growls )
Tanjiro: You should
get some rest, Inosuke.
( Inosuke growls )
Tanjiro: Sorry to ask
too much of you.
Inosuke: Huh?!
Don't underestimate me, damn it!
I can Bury 100, no, 200 bodies!
I'm gonna do way more work
than any of you! Just watch!
( Snarls )
( Yelling )
Teruko: What's
that strange man doing?
Kiyoshi: Just look
the other way.
( Shoichi grunts )
( Crow cawing )
Descend the mountain!
( Cawing )
Shoichi: Is that crow
talking to us?
Kiyoshi: This is all
a bit too much.
Teruko: Yeah.
Crow: All right, everyone!
It's time to follow yours truly!
( Caws )
( Inosuke grunts )
Huh?
¶
hey! Where are you going?
Tanjiro: Uh,
we're descending the mountain.
Inosuke: But we're not done
with our battle yet.
Tanjiro: You're tired,
aren't you?
Come on. We're heading down.
Inosuke: What?!
I'm not tired at all!
Let's fight!
( Crow cawing )
Zenitsu: No, you can't!
I won't allow it!
Don't go, shoichi!
Please, you gotta stay with us!
I've seen how powerful you are!
I need you around
to protect me from danger!
Tanjiro: Stop it!
He's obviously not interested!
Zenitsu: Don't leave me behind,
shoichi! I beg you!
Tanjiro: Stop that this instant!
( Zenitsu gurgles )
( Crow caws )
Hold out your hands!
( Both gasp )
( Crow gags )
( Kiyoshi screams )
Crow: That will ward off demons.
As the one with marechi, be sure
to keep that on your person.
Tanjiro: It smells
like Wisteria.
Kiyoshi: What's that?
Tanjiro: A flower
demons can't stand.
Make sure not to lose it.
Crow: It's a demon repellent.
It will keep them at bay.
( Inosuke snarls )
Kiyoshi: Tanjiro,
thank you for everything.
We can all get home
on our own now.
Tanjiro: Safe travels.
( Inosuke snarls )
Crow: Now, everyone, follow me!
Follow yours truly!
( Caws )
- ( Zenitsu wails )
- ( Snores )
Inosuke: Come on, and fight me!
I swear I'm gonna find
your weak point
and bring you down!
Tanjiro: I have a name,
you know.
It's Tanjiro kamado!
All right, gonpachiro kamaboko,
I'm gonna bring you down!
Tanjiro: Who are
you talking about?
- Inosuke: You, of course!
- Tanjiro: No, you're not!
Zenitsu: 'Scuse me!
Could you keep it down, please?!
( Tanjiro grunts )
( Owl hoots )
( Birds trilling )
Tanjiro: A Wisteria
family crest.
( Crow caws )
It's time to rest!
You've all had a tough day!
Rest up now!
Tanjiro: Huh?
Are you sure that's okay?
Now that you mention it,
I have been fighting
with injuries this whole time.
( Crow chortles )
Tanjiro: Is that a laugh or...
Inosuke: Let's eat this thing.
Crow: What?
Woman: Yes?
Tanjiro: Oh. Sorry to bother you
this late at night.
Zenitsu: A ghost! It's a ghost!
Tanjiro: Quiet!
- Inosuke: Who the hell are you?
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Woman: Should I presume
that you are all demon slayers?
Inosuke: We are.
What's it to you?
Tanjiro: Inosuke!
Woman: Please come in.
¶
Zenitsu: That little old lady
sure walks fast.
Woman: This is
where you'll be staying.
A change of clothes
to cleanse your body.
And a warm meal
to cleanse your soul.
Zenitsu: She has
to be a monster!
Preparing all this so quickly?
There's no way she's human!
She can't be!
She's a monster grandm--
( Inosuke gobbling )
Zenitsu: Use your chopsticks.
( Inosuke growls )
( Laughs )
( Zenitsu groans )
Tanjiro: Uh...
If you're really
that hungry, Inosuke,
go ahead and have
this bowl as well.
Inosuke: Huh?
( Wails )
Tanjiro: Take it.
Inosuke: I refuse!
Zenitsu: Is this moron for real?
He's forgotten all about the box
that was so important
to him earlier.
Give me a break!
( Inosuke snarls )
Woman: Your bedding
is ready, gentlemen.
Zenitsu: Again! The monst--
- ( groans )
- ( Inosuke laughs )
I'm takin' this one here.
First come, first serve!
Tanjiro: That's fine.
You can sleep wherever you want.
( Inosuke groans )
Tanjiro: Which one
do you want, Zenitsu?
- Zenitsu: Uh...
- ( Inosuke yells )
Zenitsu: Why me?!
Woman: Our doctor
is ready to see you.
Doctor: Greetings.
Hmm.
Yes.
I see.
Well, it's bad.
Zenitsu: Who would have guessed?
All three of us
have broken ribs.
This bump, though,
hurts a lot more.
Tanjiro: Sorry.
Zenitsu: 'Scuse me.
Where my apology?
I'm hurting, too.
You beat the crap
out of me earlier.
You sorry?
Inosuke: Not really.
Zenitsu: Just apologize!
- Inosuke: Forget it.
- Tanjiro: Hey, be nice.
Zenitsu: Look, Inosuke,
we just won't eat with you
if you act that way.
Inosuke: Huh?
How's that related?
Zenitsu: Because meals
always taste better
when you eat together,
you know?
Tanjiro: Yeah, he's right.
Inosuke: Did the two of you
hit your heads or something?
Zenitsu: Like you're one
to talk about that!
Woman: Do you need
any assistance in there?
Zenitsu: Ahh! The monster!
Tanjiro: Stop that!
( Groans )
According
to what the crow told me,
this house
with the Wisteria family crest
belongs to a family that was
once rescued by demon slayers.
That's the reason they're
housing us free of charge here.
Still, I didn't think they would
show us this much kindness.
Inosuke: Pays to be with
the demon slayer corps, huh?
Tanjiro: Now that
I think about it,
what made you decide
to join the group?
Inosuke: Huh?
Zenitsu: Well, you must
have had some kind of reason.
Inosuke: A member
of the demon slayer corps
barged in on me
on my mountain,
so we competed
to see who was stronger.
I took his blade as a reward.
( Both groan )
Zenitsu: I feel sorry
for that guy
Inosuke: And then I heard
of this thing
called "final selection"
and the fact
that demons really do exist.
Tanjiro: So that's what drew you
to the demon slayer corps.
And, hey, you grew up
in the mountains.
Same goes for me.
Inosuke:
Don't lump me in with you!
I don't have anyone
I could call family.
Only one thing gives me
comfort in this world,
and that's testing
my strength against others!
Tanjiro: Is that so? How sad.
( Zenitsu groans )
Hey, Tanjiro,
there's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
You're traveling with a demon.
What is that about?
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
Tanjiro: Zenitsu, you knew,
and you still protected the box.
You really are a good person.
You know that?
Thank you.
( Zenitsu gasps )
You don't have
to compliment me like that.
( Giggles )
Tanjiro: I've got
a keen sense of smell.
That's how I knew
from the start.
You're a kind person,
Zenitsu, strong, too.
Zenitsu: Hey, I'm not
that strong. Give me a break.
That's why I wanted
to bring shoichi along with us,
but you ruined it.
Tanjiro: Uh, but i--
that's--well...
( Thumping )
( Zenitsu shrieks )
Wh-what's happening?!
Is it coming after us now?
Tanjiro: You don't
have to worry.
Zenitsu:
How can you be so sure?!
- How?! How?!
- Tanjiro: Quiet down.
It's the middle
of the night, Zenitsu.
Inosuke: Why won't
he take the bait?
I took his food and everything.
Come to think of it,
what exactly was it
that got him so mad before?
I forget.
( Thump )
( Zenitsu shrieks )
It's not even locked?!
- You're kidding me?!
- Tanjiro: Shh!
Zenitsu: P-p-protect me!
Someone please protect me!
Even you'll do, Inosuke!
Inosuke: Stay away from me!
( Zenitsu groans )
( Squeals )
It's escaped!
( Yells )
I-I gotta hide! I'm so scared!
Nezuko: Hmm?
Zenitsu: Huh?
Tanjiro: Hey, Nezuko.
( Nezuko sighing )
Zenitsu: Huh?
¶
( Nezuko grunts )
( Zenitsu gasping )
( Inosuke grunts )
( Snorts )
( Groans ) That's enough
activity for one day.
( Snoring )
Tanjiro: I'll introduce you.
- Nezuko is my--
- Zenitsu: Tanjiro.
Tanjiro: Huh?
¶
Zenitsu: You didn't.
Tanjiro: Hey, what's wrong?
( Electricity crackling )
Zenitsu: Tell me you didn't.
Just who do you think you are?
( Tanjiro gasps )
Zenitsu: You've been
traveling with a girl...
This adorable?
Hanging around with someone
this cute day in and day out
and been having a great time
in the process, haven't you?
Tanjiro: Wait a minute.
That's not--
Zenitsu: Well, then, why did I
bear all that pain
and suffering?!
Tanjiro, you jerk!
You getting to be all, "ooh,"
and, "mwah," with a cutie
is not what I
was toiling away for!
I did not put myself
in harm's way
to get pummeled and kicked
around by a crazy boar guy!
Tanjiro: Zenitsu, calm down!
What has gotten into you?
Zenitsu: Did you think
I joined the demon slayer corps
because I thought it was gonna
be all sunshine and rainbows?
- Tanjiro: Well, i--
- Zenitsu: Guys like you
should be erased
from this world immediately!
I will finally make you pay
for thwarting my marriage,
as well as sending my savior
and protector shoichi home.
You shall face justice!
Don't ever disrespect the corps!
- ( Inosuke snoring )
- Zenitsu: You fiend!
How could you! ( Screams )
Tanjiro: Zenitsu, cut it out!
Zenitsu:
Mock the demon slayers corps,
and you'll get sent
straight to hell!
You shall feel my wrath!
¶
( singing in Japanese )