¶
( Nezuko grunts )
( Zenitsu gasping )
Tanjiro.
Tanjiro: Huh?
¶
- Zenitsu: You didn't.
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Zenitsu: Did you think
I joined the Demon Slayer Corps
because I thought it was gonna
be all sunshine and rainbows?!
- Tanjiro: Well, i--
- Zenitsu: Guys like you
should be erased
from this world immediately!
You shall face justice!
Don't ever disrespect the Corps!
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Birds squawking )
( Door creaks )
( Nezuko groaning )
Zenitsu: Hi, Nezuko!
Nezuko: Hmm?
( Zenitsu laughs )
How are you today?
( Giggles )
Nezuko: Hmm?
( Zenitsu laughs )
( Nezuko gasps )
Zenitsu:
Where are you going, Nezuko?
( Laughs )
Wait for me!
- ( Tanjiro grunts )
- Zenitsu: Uh...
Tanjiro: Zenitsu,
stop following her already!
( Zenitsu sighs )
Tanjiro...
( Giggling )
( Tanjiro wails )
Zenitsu: Let's be
best friends, Tanjiro!
Tanjiro: Zenitsu, why are you
following us around like this?
- Stop it!
- Zenitsu: Oh, come on,
don't be a stranger, Tanjiro!
Nezuko! Tanjiro!
Tanjiro: You've got
to cut this out right now!
Zenitsu: Nezuko!
- ( Stomach gurgles )
- Tanjiro!
- Inosuke: Man, I'm hungry.
- Tanjiro: Come on!
Woman: Pardon me, good sir.
¶
I cannot help but notice
those clothes of yours
are rather soiled.
It would be my pleasure
to clean them for you,
so please wear these
in the meantime.
I believe you
will find them comfortable
and pleasant to the touch.
( Inosuke sighs )
Woman: I was thinking
of making
some tempura for dinner,
you know,
something covered in batter
and fried to a golden brown.
( Inosuke sighs )
Zenitsu: Hey, wait up, you two!
Come back here, Nezuko!
- Tanjiro, where are you going?
- ( Inosuke wails )
( Boys gasp )
- ( Inosuke grunts )
- ( Tanjiro groans )
Wh-what was that for?
( Inosuke screams )
( All gasp )
Tanjiro: Hey, hey!
Don't you start
chasing us now, too, Inosuke!
- (Inosuke laughs )
- Zenitsu: Save me, Tanjiro!
¶
( birds chirping )
Doctor: All better.
( Boys sighing )
( Crow caws )
It is north-northeast!
To the north-northeast!
Your next mission
is north-northeast!
The three of you
are to go to Mount Natagumo!
Make your way there posthaste!
( Inosuke and Zenitsu sigh )
Tanjiro: We're heading out.
Thank you for everything.
Woman: I'll bestow
good luck upon you.
Tanjiro: We appreciate it.
Inosuke: Huh?
What do you think you're doing?!
( Zenitsu yells )
Stop that, you idiot!
Inosuke: What did you say?!
Zenitsu: It's ceremonial!
We're going on a journey,
and striking sparks is for luck!
¶
woman: Always live
your lives in a fashion
where you are able
to hold your heads up high.
I wish you luck in battle.
( Inosuke sighs )
¶
"heads up high"?
"Luck in battle"?
What's that mean?
Zenitsu: Jeez,
this guy is totally clueless.
Tanjiro: To be honest,
it is a little bit
difficult to explain.
"To hold your head high,"
I guess it means, whatever hand
you're given in this life,
you're able to conduct yourself
in a way that's honorable
so you're never ashamed.
Inosuke: Huh?
Tanjiro: And wishing us
luck in battle
just means
she's praying for our safety.
Inosuke: Well, what about
the "hand you're given"?
We have two already!
And why should we be ashamed?
- Tanjiro: Well, I guess--
- Inosuke: What does it mean
to conduct yourself
honorably, anyway?
And why is that old hag
praying for our safety
in the first place?
She has nothing to do with us,
so what's her game, huh?
Tanjiro: Uh...
Inosuke: Maybe she should
worry about her own hands!
- ( Both gasp )
- Zenitsu: He sped up!
( Inosuke growls )
Is this a race?
I won't let you win!
Zenitsu: Wait for me, you two!
¶
Everyone!
We need to pause here.
Tanjiro: Zenitsu? What's wrong?
Zenitsu: I'm nervous, okay?!
Now that we're nearing
our destination,
I'm getting scared!
Inosuke: Why the hell
is he sitting like that?
It's pretty weird,
if you ask me.
Zenitsu: Who are you
to talk to me about weird?
You can't tell me
you're not getting
any spooky vibes
from that mountain!
Inosuke: Huh?
¶
Tanjiro: Even so,
we can't exactly just wait here.
Inosuke: I told you
this guy's an odd duck.
Zenitsu: I am not an odd duck!
I'm completely normal!
It's you guys
that are the strange ones!
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Grunts )
( Breeze blows )
¶
Zenitsu: Tanjiro?
There something wrong?
Tanjiro: What is this smell?
Zenitsu: Tanjiro! Hey!
Wait up!
Don't leave me here by myself!
Who knows what'll happen?!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Both gasp )
( Swordsman gasping )
Help me. Please, help me.
Tanjiro: Look at his uniform.
That boy, he's one of us!
( Zenitsu panting )
Hey, don't leave me behind!
Tanjiro: Are you all right?
What happened?
( Wires creak )
- ( Demon Slayer gasps )
- ( Both gasp )
( Demon Slayer gasps )
They were attached to me, too!
Please don't let me die here!
( Zenitsu whimpers )
( Wind blowing )
Tanjiro: I'm going in.
Inosuke: I'll head in first.
You stay behind me, trembling
like a scared little animal.
This is making me hungry.
Tanjiro: Inosuke.
Zenitsu: Why is he
such a showoff?
( Inosuke cackles )
Let's go!
( Zenitsu gasps )
( Whimpering )
¶
( spiders skitter )
( Wires creaking )
( Footsteps crunching )
( Inosuke sputters )
Huh?
What is this?
Tanjiro: A spider web?
Inosuke: This place
is full of 'em,
as far as the eye can see!
What a pain!
Tanjiro: Yeah, you're right.
Inosuke?
Inosuke: What do you want?
- Tanjiro: I appreciate this.
- Inosuke: What?
Tanjiro: When you said you'd
go check things out with me,
- I was relieved.
- Inosuke: Huh?
Tanjiro: That ominous scent I
was picking up from the mountain
scared me a bit, so having you
here makes me feel better.
So thanks.
( Inosuke sighs )
Woman: I believe
you will find them
comfortable and pleasant
to the touch.
Always live your lives
in a fashion
where you are able
to hold your heads up high.
I wish you luck in battle.
( Inosuke sighs )
- Tanjiro: Inosuke.
- ( Inosuke gasps )
( Tanjiro grunts ) Let's go.
We've come to help out.
I'm Tanjiro Kamado,
rank mizunoto.
Demon Slayer 2:
A mizunoto? You serious?
They should have
sent us a hashira.
No matter how many mizunoto they
send in, it won't be enough!
- ( Inosuke growls )
- ( Demon Slayer 2 groans )
Tanjiro: Inosuke!
Inosuke: Ah, shut up!
The only thing I see
around here that's not enough
is this sputtering
pool of sweat in front of me!
Now, how 'bout you tell us
just what is going on here!
Demon Slayer 2: Who do you
think you're talking to?
Did you forget
that I have seniority?
The crow gave us orders
to come to this place,
and ten of us Corps members
gathered here.
¶
not long after
we entered the mountain,
that's when it started.
¶
( Demon Slayer 3 groans )
( Demon Slayer 2 gasps )
( Narrating ) The slayers
began killing each other.
( Overlapping yells, screams )
Demon Slayer 2: I...
( Woman vocalizing )
Demon Slayer 2: I was so...
( Crow gasping )
Demon Slayer 4:
You did well to return.
It would appear that...
Most of my children
have been killed.
We may very well find
the twelve kizuki there.
It would seem I'll
have to send in some hashira.
¶
Giyu...
And Shinobu.
( Shinobu chuckles )
Both: Understood.
¶
Shinobu:
If only humans and demons
could get along
with each other.
Wouldn't you agree, tomioka?
Giyu: That's a pipe dream,
as long as demons hunt us.
Zenitsu: I wonder
if the others hate me.
Would someone normally leave
their friend behind like this?
You'd talk him through it
if you were close, wouldn't you?
If they both had tried to
convince me to go, I would have.
- Inosuke: It's all right.
- Zenitsu: I'm sure of it.
But instead, they both
went on their merry way
up that scary mountain,
leaving poor, little me
all alone.
( Sparrow chirping )
( Zenitsu gasps )
( Sighs )
You don't have a care
in the world, do you?
All our human problems,
you have no idea.
- ( Sparrow chirps )
- Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
You think you're
being cute right now?!
Well, you're really not!
I don't like
this side of you one tiny bit!
Why can't you take some notes
from Nezuko, huh?!
She's adorable,
and she's a Demon!
Huh? ( Screams )
I just realized
he took Nezuko along with him!
Why did he have to go
and take my precious Nezuko
with him like that?!
Damn you, Tanjiro!
Taking a young girl like her
into danger?
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
I'll save you, Nezuko!
( Wires creaking )
Tanjiro: That rattling sound,
what is it?
- Demon Slayer: Not again.
- Tanjiro: Huh?
Demon Slayer:
I've heard this sound before.
It's the sound I heard
the moment before everyone
started to kill each other.
Tanjiro: Where's it coming from?
( Creaking continues )
( Chorus vocalizing )
- ( Demon Slayer gasps )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
( All gasp )
¶
( Demon Slayer yelling )
( Wires creaking )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Inosuke laughs )
These guys morons or somethin'?
They don't know that it's taboo
for us Demon slayers
to fight each other!
Tanjiro: That's not it!
They're acting odd,
like they're being manipulated.
Inosuke: Here we go.
I'm gonna cut 'em to pieces!
Tanjiro: You can't do that!
They're alive!
At least, I believe some are.
Besides, the bodies
of the ones who aren't
are still our teammates!
Inosuke: Listen, you.
Stop denying me at every turn!
( Tanjiro groans )
( Demon Slayer gasping )
( Straining )
( Tanjiro gasps )
I caught a strange,
sweet scent from his back.
It's threads! They're being
controlled by threads!
Cut them off!
( Inosuke chuckles )
( Yells )
I already knew about that
before you caught on.
Tanjiro: Where's the location
of the Demon controlling them?
( Breeze blows )
( Gasps )
What's that revolting odor?
Was just for a second, though.
( Spiders skittering )
Spiders?
( Demon laughs )
( Tanjiro gasps )
I get it!
The spiders
are just attaching people
to the puppet strings.
That means...
( Webs creaking )
( Demon laughs )
Now listen closely,
my precious little dolls.
Dance until
your arms and legs fall off.
Tanjiro: Cutting the threads
isn't enough.
The spiders
will just replace them.
So we--( Gags )
That horrible smell again.
What is it?
It's coming from far away.
Inosuke: So all we gotta do
is annihilate
those damn insects, huh?
Tanjiro: No way!
They're too small,
and there's gotta be
at least a million of them.
We gotta find the Demon
who's controlling them instead!
Inosuke: Gotcha!
( Grunting )
Tanjiro: It's no good, Inosuke.
Listen, if you have
some kind of power
that can pinpoint
the Demon's location,
that would really help!
This disgusting smell
has been blowing in,
but I just can't tell
where it's from!
You there, your name?!
Demon Slayer: Murata!
Tanjiro: Murata, the two of us
will take care of
the people being controlled.
In the meantime...
¶
( gasps )
( Webs creaking )
Demon 2:
I will not let you disturb
my family's peaceful life.
Tanjiro: He's floating?
No. He's standing
on the threads.
His family?
Demon 2: Mother will be sure
to make quick work
of all of you.
Tanjiro: Who's mother?
( Inosuke growling )
Damn you!
Where the hell do you think
you're going? Fight me!
Fight--( Gags )
Tanjiro: You all right, Inosuke?
Inosuke: Why did he
even show up, anyway?
Tanjiro: I don't think
he's the Demon
who's controlling our people
with those threads.
We can't focus on him now.
Zenitsu: Okay, okay, okay!
I get it, all right?
You want me
to go find the one who is!
Shut up about it already!
( Growls )
Beast breathing.
Seventh form,
spatial awareness!
¶
( Breathing deeply )
I've found you, you Demon!
¶
Demon 2: I won't let
anyone get in our way.
The five of us are going to live
in happiness as a family.
No one on this mortal plane
will tear us apart.
¶
( singing in Japanese )