¶
( yahaba growls )
Time for you to die!
( Yells )
Twist! Envelop!
Twisting whirlpool!
Flowing water!
( Yahaba groans )
( Tanjiro groaning )
My sword is so heavy.
But I've got this!
Second form improved!
Lateral water wheel!
( Yahaba gags )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Yahaba gags )
( Tanjiro grunts )
I did it.
The whirlpool isn't as strong
when it's not underwater,
but I used his attack to gain
power and envelop the arrows.
( Yahaba groans )
You damn brat!
How could you do this to me?!
I just needed
to bring him your head.
That's all it would have taken
to finally win his approval!
I'll never forgive you.
I'll make sure you pay
for what you've done to me!
My face is filthy because of
you shoving it into the dirt!
I swear I'll
bring you down with me!
( Tanjiro gasps )
Oh, no! He's got me!
( Gasps )
This force is stronger
than any of the arrows
he's hit me with before.
Have to defend myself
with every move I've got,
or my body'll be smashed!
Fourth form!
Striking tide!
( Grunting )
My body's
under so much pressure,
I can't swing my sword!
Do something.
Make a move!
Don't get beaten, not here!
Second form! Water wheel!
( Singers vocalizing )
( Yelps )
Waterfall basin!
( Yells )
Surface slash!
Drop ripple thrust!
Sixth form! Whirlpool!
I've never used
so many moves in a row before.
It feels like my arms
are gonna get ripped off.
Yahaba: You haven't
suffered enough.
I'm not done, not just yet.
Your pain will be excruciating.
¶
Tanjiro: How long
will this go on?
When will it end?
Don't think about it!
Just keep fighting back!
Pull out all the stops!
Yahaba: Still not enough.
Not yet! I still haven't--
( Tanjiro groans )
( Panting )
( Grunting )
Nezuko.
Miss tamayo.
Yushiro.
( Groans )
I cracked my rib
and broke my leg.
I-It's no use.
I'm so exhausted,
I can't even grip my sword.
I gotta go--
I gotta get over there.
There's one more demon left.
Hang on. I'm coming.
I'll be there soon.
Just hang on.
I'm coming. Stay safe!
( Singers vocalizing )
( Susamaru laughs )
( Yushiro gasps )
What a fool!
Avoiding a bunch
of linear attacks like these
is child's play!
Finding you will be easy, too!
( Susamaru laughs )
And finding you
will be a piece of cake.
You may be good
at that concealment spell,
but I know right where you are!
( Laughs )
Now's when the real fun starts!
- ( Nezuko grunts )
- Yushiro: Don't do that!
You can't be reckless
just because you're immortal!
Uh, what is it?
( Gasps )
What are you doing?! Watch out!
( Susamaru laughs )
Yushiro: Amazing.
Lady tamayo.
( Nezuko kicks temari )
( Susamaru gasps )
¶
you little brat.
You think you're tough,
just because you figured out how
to kick my temari back at me?
Don't be so arrogant!
( Temari rings )
( Susamaru growls )
Damn you, you brat!
( Nezuko growls )
Yushiro: But how?
Lady tamayo,
what did you do to her?
Tamayo: I just gave her
a healing serum
made specifically for demons,
but all it did was heal her.
It has no effect
on her physical strength.
We're witnessing nezuko's power.
Without even a drop
of human blood, this is all her.
( Singers vocalizing )
She's rapidly gaining strength.
( Nezuko growling )
( Susamaru gasps )
Tamayo: But her opponent
is formidable.
If she gave it her all,
nezuko wouldn't stand a chance.
She needs help.
Let's see what I can do.
( Susamaru laughs )
Aren't you
an amusing little girl?
Looks like I'm going to have to
give this everything I've got.
- ( Temari rings )
- I'm curious to see
how long you can hold out.
( Nezuko growls )
Tamayo: If you're
a twelve kizuki,
I have a question.
Get out of the way.
Move it, you damn fugitive.
Tamayo: One question,
that's all I'm asking.
Do you have any idea
who kibutsuji really is?
Susamaru: Huh?
What the hell are you saying?!
Tamayo: He's a coward.
Surely you've realized that.
He's in a constant
state of fear.
Susamaru: How dare you?
Damn you! Shut up!
Tamayo: Do you want to know
why no demons
can ever group together
or why they cannibalize
each other?
Because he doesn't
want us to group up.
His fear is that we
would attack him if we could.
He manipulates demons
to make them behave,
demons like you.
Susamaru: Don't you dare.
Don't say that! Shut up!
He has no reason
to be so petty!
( Yushiro gasps ) Of course.
Lady tamayo is casting a spell.
Susamaru: You can't comprehend
the power he wields!
No one's stronger than him,
not lord kibutsuji!
¶
( gasps )
Tamayo: You forgot you couldn't
say his name, didn't you?
You just triggered the curse.
( Susamaru whimpers )
Yushiro: Magical aroma
of daylight.
It weakens
the target's brain functions,
making it impossible
for them to lie or keep secrets.
And it's so potent.
Lady tamayo.
Tamayo: I feel sorry for you.
But farewell now.
( Susamaru gasping )
( Wails )
Please forgive me!
I'm so sorry!
I'm begging you!
I didn't mean to!
Please forgive me!
- ( Sobs )
- ( Temari ringing )
( Tanjiro grunting )
( Susamaru groaning )
( Screams )
( Gagging )
( Wind blowing )
( Yushiro shuddering )
( Susamaru weeping )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Squelching, cracking )
( Squelching,
cracking continue )
¶
Tanjiro: Is it all over?
Is she dead?
Tamayo: She will be momentarily.
Kibutsuji's curse.
The cells he left in her body
will destroy it.
She'll be ripped apart
from the inside.
Generally speaking, a battle
between demons is futile.
It's pointless.
The wounds they inflict
on each other can't be fatal.
Only sunlight or the sword
of a demon slayer can kill them.
Except kibutsuji.
He's the only one
who can destroy a demon's cells.
( Tanjiro sighs )
( Running footsteps )
( Gasps )
Yushiro: You can't inhale
lady tamayo's spell.
The human body can't take it.
You got that?
( Tanjiro grunts )
Tamayo: Tanjiro...
The demon we fought,
she's not
one of the twelve kizuki.
The twelve kizuki
all have numbers
engraved on their eyeballs,
but she doesn't have one,
which means that the other demon
most likely doesn't, either.
They were too weak.
Tanjiro: Hmm? Too weak? Really?!
Yushiro: Don't question her.
Lady tamayo's never wrong.
Pathetic. That demon
was incredibly stupid.
She thought she could get away
with hurting lady tamayo.
She deserved
what happened to her.
Tamayo: With any luck,
this blood will still
be instrumental for us
in developing a cure.
Now I need
to take care of nezuko.
She was already medicated,
and she inhaled my spell,
for which I'm deeply sorry.
( Yushiro gasps )
All right, don't move a muscle!
You're on your own now.
I won't leave
lady tamayo's side,
not for a second!
( Susamaru gasping )
Mari.
Tanjiro: Hmm?
Susamaru: Mari.
Mari.
( Singers vocalizing )
( Temari rings )
Tanjiro: Here's your temari.
Susamaru: Play with me.
Play with me.
Tanjiro: You probably
murdered dozens,
but, inside,
you're just a little kid.
( Birds chirping )
You thought you were
one of the twelve kizuki,
deceived, forced to fight,
and now it's kibutsuji's curse
that killed you.
No salvation.
Once you die,
not even your bones remain.
Is this the price you pay
for killing people?
( Crying )
Kibutsuji.
Even the people who follow him
get treated this way.
He truly is a demon.
Miss tamayo!
Hey, yushiro?
Yushiro: We're over here.
Tanjiro: Wha...
Yushiro: You really
don't need to come down,
but if you want to,
hurry it up.
Tamayo: Yushiro!
Yushiro: Just kidding!
Tamayo: It's all right.
Come on down, tanjiro.
Tanjiro: Oh, okay.
( Gasps ) Nezuko!
Tamayo: I thought it best
to get her down to the basement
before daybreak.
The sunlight
won't reach us here.
( Nezuko grunts )
Tanjiro: Nezuko?
( Yushiro stammers )
What are you doing?!
Step away from lady tamayo!
That's so rude!
Calm down, yushiro.
I don't mind at all.
Yushiro: Right!
You're so kind, lady tamayo,
too beautiful to believe.
( Nezuko grunts )
( Yushiro stammers )
No! Stop!
Yushiro: It's a bit strange.
She's been acting like this
ever since she woke up.
I wonder if she's all right.
Tanjiro: There's nothing
to worry about.
She's just fine.
( Yushiro stammering )
Tanjiro: If I were
to make a guess,
I'd say she thinks
of you both as family.
Yushiro: Knock it off!
Tamayo: Us as family?
But wait. I thought
the spell nezuko was under
only made her
see humans as family,
and yushiro and I are demons.
Yushiro: I said stop!
Tanjiro: Not to nezuko.
You two are as human
as anyone to her.
She wanted to protect you.
You know, I didn't like
the idea of that spell at first,
but she still seems to have
a will of her own, so...
¶
( gasps ) I'm so sorry!
Nezuko, stop it!
Get away from her!
You're being very rude!
( Tamayo sniffles )
Thank you.
Thank you so much, nezuko.
Tamayo: There is a way for me
to keep you alive, if you want.
However, it will cost you
your humanity.
If I don't do it,
you will indeed succumb
to your illness.
But beware.
If you lose your humanity,
that will cause pain as well.
So tell me.
Do you still wish to live?
( Yushiro sighs )
Tamayo: Yushiro and I
will be leaving this region.
Yushiro: Huh?
Tamayo: We're too close
to kibutsuji now.
It's far too risky to stay here.
We need a new place to hide.
Besides, I think
I've hidden my identity,
but, after treating
so many humans,
I'm sure some of them
figured out I'm a demon.
Children and the elderly
are especially perceptive.
So, tanjiro...
Tanjiro: Yes?
Tamayo: To protect nezuko,
would you like us
to take her with us when we go?
- ( Yushiro gasps )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Tamayo: Obviously
I can't promise her safety,
but I believe
she'll face less danger
than she will in battle.
Tanjiro: She might be right.
With them, wherever they end up,
nezuko would be safer.
( Gasps )
( Sighs )
( Grunts )
Miss tamayo,
thank you for your concern,
but nezuko's staying with me.
Nothing's gonna break us apart.
( Singers vocalizing )
No. Never again.
Tamayo: Yes, I understand.
Well, I wish you
good fortune, then.
Yushiro: All right.
We will be leaving
as soon as we cover our tracks.
You should get moving as well.
Tanjiro: You're right,
and good luck.
Thank you for everything
you've done for us.
- Let's go, nezuko.
- ( Nezuko grunts )
Tanjiro: Hey!
That doesn't mean
you need to run!
Yushiro: Tanjiro!
Your little sister...
I guess she is a beauty.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Laughs )
( Crow cawing )
South-southeast!
The next place you need to go
is south-southeast!
- Tanjiro: I heard you!
- ( Crow caws )
You don't have to keep
squawking it at me, okay?
- Crow: South-southeast!
- Tanjiro: I'm begging you!
I got the message, so be quiet!
- Boy: Please!
- ( Crow squawks )
( Stammers )
Boy: Please! Please! Please!
Please marry me!
You know I could die
any day now!
Marry me so I don't die alone!
Marry me!
I'm begging you, please!
- Tanjiro: Wh-what is he doing?
- ( Boy sobbing )
Tanjiro: What on earth?
¶
( singing in Japanese )