¶
Urokodaki:
Are you finished changing?
Tanjiro: Yes.
( Urokodaki grunts )
( Nezuko gasps )
( Tanjiro grunts )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Urokodaki: Tanjiro...
Now that you have officially
become a demon slayer swordsman,
I would like to explain
a few things.
- Tanjiro: Right.
- Urokodaki: First,
the demon slayer corps uniform
you're wearing
is made with
a special kind of fiber.
It's lightweight,
water resistant,
and nonflammable.
A low-level demon's
fangs and talons
are incapable
of penetrating that fabric.
Tanjiro: It's that strong?
Urokodaki: Impressive, hmm?
Now, as for the nichirin sword,
its color varies
from owner to owner,
and each hue
has its own unique traits.
However, there aren't many
demon slayers with black blades,
so little is known about them.
Some believe
they're a bad omen.
Tanjiro: What does that mean,
"bad omen"? How so?
Urokodaki: Black blades
are rumored to only be wielded
by a swordsman who has
little chance of going very far.
( Tanjiro sighs ) Oh, well.
I don't care
if I'm destined for greatness,
because, no matter what,
I'll turn nezuko back.
Urokodaki: Yes, you will.
I have no doubt
you'll make that happen.
Tanjiro: Thank you.
Urokodaki: One last thing. Here.
A box to carry your sister
during the day,
built from a very light wood
called kirikumo cedar.
It's been coated in rock lacquer
to reinforce the exterior
and make it even more durable.
Tanjiro: Thanks, urokodaki.
Oh, wow!
You weren't kidding!
It is light!
( Chuckles )
Nezuko, hop in for a ride.
Pretty please?
( Nezuko grunting )
Tanjiro: Nezuko, from now on,
we'll always be together.
Okay. I'm off.
Urokodaki: Before you go...
( Grunts )
( Tanjiro grunts )
¶
( Birds calling )
Nezuko, how you doing?
( Thumping )
Nezuko?
Urokodaki: This is only a guess,
but I believe
nezuko can recover her strength
by sleeping,
instead of consuming human flesh
as other demons do.
( Tanjiro sighs )
Okay. Rest up, nezuko.
( Distant chatter )
A town to the northwest.
Looks like I found it.
¶
woman: Oh, look. There's kazumi.
Poor thing.
He doesn't look good.
Tanjiro: Eh?
Woman 2: Well,
he was right next to satoko
when she was taken.
Man: It's happening every night.
It's very creepy.
Woman 1: Tragic. Dreadful!
Woman 2: As soon as night falls,
another girl will be abducted.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Mr. Kazumi!
I want to hear what happened
last night from you.
Kazumi: This is
where satoko vanished,
but I'm sure
you don't believe me.
Tanjiro: I do believe you.
I'm here to help.
- Now let's see!
- ( Kazumi gasps )
( Tanjiro sniffing )
There's still a faint scent
of the demon here...
( Breeze blowing )
But it's uneven.
Something's off.
Kazumi: Who is this kid, anyway?
( Grunts )
- ( Thump )
- ( Pot shatters )
( Man gasping ) How dare you?!
( Kazumi panting )
Man: You lost her?!
You bastard!
Woman: That's enough!
Honey, please, stop!
( Sobbing )
¶
( kazumi shuddering )
( Overlapping chatter )
¶
( singers vocalizing )
( Tanjiro sniffs )
( Crowd murmuring )
Kazumi: I want you
to believe me.
She really did just vanish.
Tanjiro: I know.
That's why I came here,
so I can stop this.
( Tanjiro sniffing )
Kazumi: Are you really
gonna keep going?
Tanjiro: Yes.
Kazumi: Come on.
It's getting late.
I'm flattered that you're
so concerned about this,
but shouldn't you rest,
maybe pick it up again
in the morning?
Tanjiro: They're only
active at night...
So there's no time for rest.
Got something.
There's a new scent
in the area.
It's nearby.
It won't be long now.
Kazumi: Wait a second.
Don't tell me you're a--
are you a...
( Singers vocalizing )
Woman: It's terrifying.
I want you to stay indoors,
where you'll be safe.
Girl: I will, mother.
Good night. I'm going to bed.
¶
( Flowing )
( Flows )
I wonder what happened
to the girls who disappeared.
I hope they're all right.
( Flowing )
- ( Slap )
- ( Muffled grunting )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Kazumi: Hey, wait!
Where are you going?!
So fast.
Tanjiro: The scent got stronger!
The demon's active!
Kazumi: How'd he do that?
He said, "demon."
Demon? Then he's...
¶
Tanjiro: This is it.
They're right here.
Two scents--
one demon, one human girl.
I don't see them.
Although...
( Singers vocalizing )
The scent is strongest right...
Here!
( Demon grunts )
( Flowing )
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
The demon has powers!
Urokodaki: The blood demon art
is a special spell that some use
to give them abilities.
You may end up
having to face some of them
in the near future as well.
Tanjiro: What did you do
with the girls you kidnapped?!
( Demon hissing,
grinding teeth )
Tanjiro: There are
some things I wanna know!
( Demon hissing,
grinding teeth )
( Tanjiro gasps )
- Kazumi: Who was that?
- Tanjiro: I need your help.
Hold her for me, and stay close.
As long as you do that,
I can protect you!
The ground, the wall,
I bet it could come
from just about anywhere.
I wouldn't be surprised
if it could appear
out of thin air.
Doesn't matter, because,
even if it's submerged,
it can't erase its scent.
( Sniffs )
Now.
Water breathing! Fifth form!
( Gasps ) There are more!
Take it easy.
You've got this!
Eighth form!
Waterfall basin!
¶
okodaki: Tanjiro,
listen to me closely.
There's only one demon
that has the kind of blood
that can turn a human, just one,
that's it, in the entire world.
Tanjiro: Just one?
Urokodaki: The first demon
there ever was.
He's been here
for more than a thousand years.
He's your target, the one
who attacked your family.
More importantly,
I believe he's also the one
who might know how to turn
your sister back into a human.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Urokodaki:
That demon's name is...
( Crowd screaming )
Urokodaki: Muzan kibutsuji.
Tanjiro: Eighth form!
Waterfall basin!
¶
I missed.
I missed
all the vulnerable spots,
because I switched forms
midway through.
( Kazumi gasps )
Tanjiro: They all have
the same exact scent.
Usually, demons
don't work together.
Which means one demon
has split into three.
I have to take them all out
and still protect these two.
Don't lose your nerve.
Make him talk to you
about muzan kibutsuji
and about how to turn a demon
back into a human!
- Total concentration.
- ( Kazumi gasps )
Tanjiro: Water breathing!
Second form! Water wheel!
( Demon groans )
Tanjiro: Missed again.
( Grunts )
I can't chase him,
and I can't take a full swing
while I'm protecting
these two, either.
- Demon: Bastard!
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Demon: She'll go stale!
Move out of the way,
you little punk!
The girl's 16 already.
She's losing flavor
by the second!
If I don't eat her soon,
there won't be any left at all!
( Kazumi gasps )
Demon 2:
Take a breath, other me.
Calm down. No big deal.
Nights like this happen, right?
I've already feasted
on plenty of this town's
16-year-old girls,
and every one of them
was meaty and delicious.
I am satisfied with that.
Demon 1: Well, I'm not
satisfied at all, other me!
I want to devour all of them!
Kazumi: You monster!
Bring satoko back,
the girl you took
the other night!
( Demon 3 grinding teeth,
hissing )
( Both gasp )
( Demons hissing,
grinding teeth )
Demon 2: Satoko?
Which one was that?
( Kazumi gasping )
Demon 2: If her hairpin
is in this collection,
then I'm afraid
I've already eaten her. Sorry.
¶
( Crowd screaming )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Demon hisses )
( Groans )
Tanjiro: I missed again.
He moves so fast! ( Gasps )
Oh, crap!
I'm too close to the wall!
- ( Demon 1 grunts )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
( Demon 1 babbles )
( Groans )
Demon 2: Why in the world
would a demon
be traveling with a mere human?
( Nezuko growling )
Demon 2:
What's the meaning of this?
Who are these two?
Why would a swordsman and demon
be working together?
It doesn't make any sense.
( Neck creaking )
( Nezuko panting )
( Grunts )
( Kazumi gasps )
( Gasping )
¶
Tanjiro: Nezuko.
Urokodaki: I don't know if this
will be of any comfort or not,
but while nezuko was asleep,
I used
hypnotic suggestion on her.
Tanjiro: What for?
Urokodaki: I convinced her
that all humans are her family.
I told her to protect them.
"The demons are your enemies."
( Nezuko growling )
Tanjiro: Nezuko!
Urokodaki:
"If a demon harms a human,
never forgive them!"
¶
( singing in Japanese )