( Bird squawking )
Tanjiro: Pardon me, sir.
Would it be all right
if I took that basket
and some straw and bamboo?
Man: You're more than welcome,
for all the good it'll do you.
The basket's full of holes.
Tanjiro: Thank you.
I'll gladly pay you for it.
Man: No, you don't
have to do that.
I don't need it anyway.
Tanjiro: Please, I insist.
Man: No, it's fine. Same goes
for the straw and bamboo.
Tanjiro: Let me pay you!
Man: I said it's fine,
so just take it,
you stubborn kid!
( Stammering )
Tanjiro:
Take this small offering
for your trouble, please!
And thanks a lot for your help!
Man: Gaah!
( Birds chirping )
Tanjiro: Nezuko?
Hey, nezuko?
She's gone!
- ( Nezuko grunts )
- ( Tanjiro sighs )
( Nezuko groans )
( Singing in Japanese )
( Women vocalizing )
( Birds chirping )
Tanjiro: Hey, nezuko...
¶
why'd she dig a hole?
Is my demon kid sister
turning into a mole now?
( Nezuko sighing )
Tanjiro: And she doesn't look
very happy about it, either.
Guess she really wants
to avoid the sun.
Hang on just a second.
Nezuko? Nezuko?
You think you could fit in here?
I want to try to keep moving
during the day, too,
but I can carry you, okay?
( Nezuko groans )
Tanjiro: Can you fit? In here?
( Slowly ) Bas-ket.
( Nezuko groans )
Tanjiro: Uh, guess not.
I can't believe
how grown-up she is.
Seems like yesterday
she was half that size.
Eh?
Hey, uh, nezuko,
remember how you
got really big the other day?
I've got an idea.
Do you think
you could get smaller?
Come on, nezuko.
Get smaller for me.
( Nezuko grunts )
( Grunts )
Tanjiro: Nice job!
- Who's a good girl?
- ( Nezuko chuckling )
Tanjiro: You are, nezuko.
I'm impressed.
( Bird squawks )
Woman: Mount sagiri?
If you really want to go there,
the fastest way
is over that mountain.
But the sun's about to set,
and you're hauling
an awful lot of luggage.
It's dangerous.
Tanjiro: Please don't worry.
I'll be careful.
And thank you
for the directions.
Woman: A lot of people
have been going missing
on that mountain lately!
Don't get lost, okay?
( Owl hoots )
( Tanjiro gasps )
It's a temple.
Looks like
the light's been left on,
so somebody must be there.
Let's check it out.
( Gasps )
¶
that's the scent of blood.
This path can be pretty rough.
Somebody must be hurt!
( Panting )
Is everyone okay?
( Gasps )
( Demon chewing )
( Woman vocalizing )
Demon: The hell
are you doing here?
This is my territory.
Anybody who sets foot on my turf
is gonna have to pay.
Tanjiro: It's a demon!
( Nezuko grunting )
( Chorus vocalizing )
Demon: Huh?
( Slurping )
Something's
not quite right about you.
Hang on. Are you two human?
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Demon growls )
( Chuckles )
A hatchet?
Not bad, kid.
Just a little scratch, though.
Should heal in no time.
( Squelch )
See that?
The bleeding's already stopped.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Nezuko panting )
( Woman vocalizing )
( Tanjiro grunts )
He's so fast
and insanely strong.
Demon: You got lucky,
but it won't work again.
And now I'm gonna
snap your neck!
( Chorus vocalizing )
- ( Tanjiro yelps )
- ( Nezuko gasps )
( Demon snarls )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Whahh?
( Wails )
( Nezuko panting )
Tanjiro: She--
nezuko, you killed him!
Wait a minute!
But he's a demon!
N-Nezuko.
I don't believe it.
Did that body just move
and without a head?
Demon: You bastards!
( Tanjiro gasps )
Demon: So the girl's
a demon after all, huh?
I couldn't tell with
that weird vibe you gave off.
But what are you doing
teaming up with a human?!
Tanjiro:
How's he still talking?!
¶
( nezuko panting )
Tanjiro: Leave her alone!
( Yells )
( Demon growling )
Tanjiro: Nezuko!
( Nezuko grunting )
Tanjiro: No, nezuko!
( Demon growling )
( Tanjiro gasps )
What the hell is with this guy?
Who grows arms
out of the side of their head?!
I've gotta help nezuko!
Out of the way!
( Demon gasps )
So hard.
This kid's head is...
Damn hard!
( Tanjiro yells )
( Demon babbling )
Tanjiro: Yes!
Demon: Wrapping my hair
around his hatchet
wasn't a great idea. Damn.
¶
tanjiro: Nezuko! Where are you?!
( Nezuko grunts )
Tanjiro: Nezuko!
Get away from her!
( Women vocalizing )
( Screams )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Grunts )
( Demon gags )
( Gasps )
( Birds squawking )
Tanjiro: I wonder,
how many demons are there?
This isn't the scent
I found at my house.
It's different, but...
I still have to finish him off,
or he'll keep killing people.
So that means I have to do it.
( Gasping )
Just do it.
¶
( gasps )
Man: That knife
isn't going to do the job.
Tanjiro: What's with the mask?
And I couldn't hear
his footsteps.
O-Okay.
How do I kill him, then?
Man: Think for yourself.
Or aren't you capable
of solving your own problems?
Tanjiro: Uh...
Stabbing the head won't work,
so I'll have to crush it.
¶
I probably have to crush
his skull completely,
which means hitting him
with this rock over and over.
I bet he'll suffer.
Isn't there any way for me
to finish him off with one blow?
( Man sighs )
This kid's not going to cut it.
He's far too kind
and far too indecisive.
He stands against a demon,
yet the scent
of kindness remains.
He still has empathy,
even for a demon.
Giyu, this boy
will never make it.
( Demon groans )
( Gasps )
I blacked out
for a second there.
Does that mean
that my body's dead?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
You bastard, I'll kill you!
Get over here!
I'll devour you, damn it!
Now get over here where I
can reach you, you little brat!
- Hey, aren't you...
- Tanjiro: I took too long.
The sun's already coming up.
Demon: I am gonna enjoy
eating you more than--
yaah! ( Gasps )
( Screaming )
( Tanjiro gasps )
It only takes
that much sunlight to melt him?
No wonder nezuko was hiding.
Nezuko?
Nezuko!
( Gasping )
( Sighs )
( Nezuko groans )
Nezuko: You're all right.
Eh?
Hang on. Where's the old guy?
( Footsteps approaching )
He's holding a burial
for the people who got killed.
Excuse me.
Urokodaki: My name
is sakonji urokodaki.
You're the one giyu tomioka
sent my way, correct?
( Tanjiro gasps )
I am! I'm tanjiro kamado,
and my sister's name is nezuko.
Urokodaki: Tanjiro...
What do you intend to do
if your sister eats a human?
( Tanjiro gasps )
Urokodaki:
You're too indecisive.
You must learn
to make decisions quickly.
That's why you failed to kill
that demon before daybreak.
Do you know
why it took you so long
to answer my simple question?
Because your resolve
is too weak.
There are two things you must do
if your sister eats a human.
First, you kill her.
Then slit your own belly
and die.
That's what traveling alongside
a demon like your sister means.
But you must never
allow this to happen,
no matter the cost.
Your sister taking the life
of an innocent person
is the one thing
that can't happen, ever!
Have I made myself
perfectly clear?
Tanjiro: Yes!
Urokodaki: Very well.
I will test
whether or not you are fit
to become a member
of the demon slayer corps.
Carry your sister,
and follow me!
( Tanjiro panting )
¶
So fast. But I thought
he was an old man!
And, still, I can't hear
his footsteps at all!
Nezuko, the ride may be bumpy,
but just hang on.
But then, you always
did know how to be patient.
Didn't you, nezuko?
Fixing your kimono again?
That settles it.
We'll have to buy you a new one.
Nezuko: No, no,
it's fine, really!
This kimono is my favorite.
Besides, it's not important.
I'd rather feed
our brothers and sisters.
( Giggles )
Tanjiro: I swear, I'll turn you
back into a human,
and then I'm gonna buy you
a beautiful kimono!
Everything I wasn't able
to do for the others,
I'll do it all for you!
( Panting )
Okay. Does this--
does this mean--
please tell me this means
that I passed the test.
Urokodaki:
We're just beginning the test.
We'll be climbing a mountain.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Urokodaki: I promise I'll
take care of your sister for you
while you're gone.
Tanjiro: I do
appreciate that, sir.
( Bird warbles )
( Animal bugles )
( Tanjiro panting )
Oh, man.
I'm so exhausted,
my legs are starting to buckle,
and I'm getting dizzy, too.
Urokodaki: Now find your way
back to my house
at the foot of the mountain.
This time,
I won't wait until daybreak.
( Wind gusting )
Tanjiro: Huh?
That's the test?
Uh...
I get it.
Because of the fog,
he thinks I might get lost.
All I have to do
is get back by daybreak?
No problem,
not with my sense of smell.
I've memorized
Mr. Urokodaki's scent.
( Gasps )
( Grunts ) What the?!
( Yells )
( Birds flapping, squawking )
( Groaning )
A tiger pit?
Of course.
There are traps
all over the mountain.
That's why this is a test.
( Gasps ) Oh, no!
( Grunts )
Crap, crap, crap.
If I keep
walking into these traps,
I'll never make it
down the mountain by morning.
Not to mention,
besides the traps,
the air here is--
the air is thin
on this mountain,
a whole lot thinner than
on the mountain where I grew up.
It's no wonder I feel so dizzy.
I can't breathe.
I hope I can make it.
I might pass out.
No, I have to make it!
Control your breathing.
Then sniff out
all of those traps.
¶
( Gasps )
( Grunting )
Yes, got it!
Piece of cake!
These traps were set by a human,
which means their scent
sticks out to me!
But I guess...
That doesn't solve
all my problems,
because i'm
still not athletic enough
to dodge
every single one of them!
I'll make it back,
no matter what...
For nezuko!
¶
( Panting )
I made it...
Back down.
Giyu: Dear urokodaki, sir,
forgive the intrusion.
There's a boy headed your way
in need of instruction.
He wants to be a demon slayer.
He was fearless enough
to try to attack me unarmed.
A demon killed his family,
except for his younger sister,
who's been turned,
but I'm certain
she will not attack a human.
They're different.
I can sense
something about these two.
The boy has a keen sense
of smell, much like yourself.
So maybe, just maybe,
he'll be able to find a way
to break through.
I'm asking for you
to train this boy.
This may seem
like a frivolous request,
but please humor me.
If I'm not mistaken,
this will all
make sense one day.
Take care of yourself.
Yours truly, giyu tomioka.
( Tanjiro breathing heavily )
Urokodaki: You're now
my new student, tanjiro kamado.
( Singing in Japanese )