¶
Shinobu: Heading into battle?
Rengoku: Hmm?
Ah, Kocho!
We got new intel on a demon.
The slayer who found it
was defeated.
We're losing
rank and filers now.
We have to act!
Shinobu: Could it be
a twelve kizuki?
Rengoku: Most likely.
Maybe an upper rank.
Shinobu: It sounds
like a difficult mission,
but as long
as you're going, Rengoku,
we don't have to worry.
Rengoku: And you?
What's the plan,
taking that head-butting kid in?
You had mentioned
recruiting more tsuguko,
but I doubt that's the reason.
Shinobu: You seem concerned.
You don't think I'm going
to gobble him up, do you?
Rengoku: Of course I don't!
( Laughing )
Shinobu: Do be careful.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Zenitsu: No!
I can't possibly take
any more of this!
Woman:
We go through this every day.
Saying you're in bad shape
is an understatement.
Take your medicine this second!
( Zenitsu whimpers )
Woman: Good grief.
Tanjiro,
this medicine is for you.
Girl: Here you go.
Tanjiro: Thank you very much.
Zenitsu: Hey!
I saw that medicine
go down much easier!
So then,
it's different from mine?
Favoritism!
I call favoritism here!
Tanjiro: Zenitsu, quiet down!
This is a hospital ward!
- Murata: You all seem lively.
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
( Gasps )
Murata!
Murata: Hey!
( Zenitsu gags )
Tanjiro: How have
you been doing?
Murata: I came this close
to getting melted down,
but I survived somehow.
I hear you guys got banged up
pretty good, though.
Tanjiro: Yeah, it's gonna
take time for us to bounce back.
Murata: What was it
that happened to you, boar kid?
Hmm? Is he sleeping
or something?
Tanjiro: He went through a lot.
You should just let him be.
Murata: But for him,
of all people, to be quiet...
- Zenitsu: Tanjiro!
- Tanjiro: Eh?
Zenitsu: Who is this?
Tanjiro: He fought with us
on mount natagumo.
He's a friend.
Murata: I'm Murata.
Nice to meet you.
What happened to your arms?
Zenitsu: My limbs shrunk down,
because I was almost
turned into a spider.
Woman: And that's why
you need to take this medicine.
Zenitsu: Agh!
But it tastes so gross!
There's only so much gross
a person can take!
Woman: Don't come crying to me
if your arms
don't go back to normal!
Zenitsu: So cruel! That's
such a cruel thing to say!
Woman: You don't know
how good you have it!
You realize,
if you take this medicine
and get lots of sunlight,
there'll be no lasting effects,
don't you?
Zenitsu: I can't do it!
None of that changes the fact
that stuff tastes awful!
( Murata chuckles )
Sounds like fun. Lucky you.
Tanjiro: What do you mean?
Murata: I was summoned
to the hashira meeting
to give my report on everything
that related
to the mount natagumo incident.
It felt like hell.
Those hashira
are absolutely terrifying!
They were all really furious
about how the quality
of the new demon slayers
had gone downhill,
because there were
a number of us
who neglected to follow orders
during what happened up there.
They were asking me things like,
"who trained them, anyway?"
What good was it
asking a no-rank like me
into a meeting like that?
( Tanjiro and Zenitsu gasp )
Murata:
The hashira really terrify me.
Shinobu: Hello there.
( Murata gasps )
Lady--Lady Kocho!
Shinobu: Good day to you.
Murata: You as well! Goodbye!
Shigeru: Oh, my.
Leaving so soon?
The two of you,
how are you feeling?
Tanjiro: I think
we're a lot better now.
Shinobu:
Well, if that's the case,
let's have you start
your rehabilitation training.
Tanjiro:
Our "rehabilitation training"?
Shinobu: Yes!
Inosuke: Forgive me
for being weak.
Zenitsu: Tanjiro and Inosuke
were taken away by Lady Kocho,
and started something
called rehabilitation training.
The sound Shinobu gives off
is totally unique.
I don't think
I've heard anything like it.
There's something about it
that's a little unnerving.
But when she
was treating the people
who got turned into spiders,
she seemed ethereal.
It's no wonder
everyone ran to her in tears.
Doesn't hurt
she's as pretty as a picture.
I bet she could get by
on her looks alone.
So Lady Kocho
took Tanjiro and Inosuke
to rehabilitation training
to rebuild their strength,
which means...
( Door slides )
( Both groan )
Zenitsu: They're gonna
come back looking like that.
Hey, welcome back, you two!
How did it go today?
¶
what's the matter?
Did something happen?
Tanjiro: Sorry.
Inosuke: Don't mind us.
Zenitsu: Please tell me!
I'm gonna be
in the same boat as you two
starting tomorrow!
I need to be mentally prepared!
Please!
Zenitsu: Scared. Scared.
I'm so scared!
I don't wanna go!
Woman: All right, Zenitsu,
since you'll be
joining us starting today,
I will explain
the training regimen again.
- You will begin there.
- ( Girls huff )
Woman: Those girls will get your
bedridden bodies limber again.
( Inosuke grunts, groaning )
( Girl grunting )
Woman: Next, reflex training.
These cups
contain medicated water.
The objective
is to throw that water
onto the other person,
but there's a twist.
Your opponent
is able to block you
from picking up your cup.
¶
- go!
- ( Tanjiro grunts )
Woman: Again!
- Go!
- ( Tanjiro chuckles )
( Grunts )
Woman: That's enough!
Last, full-body training.
Or put simply, a game of tag.
You will face myself, aoi,
and then Kanao.
( Boys sigh )
Zenitsu: Excuse me.
May I say something?
Aoi: Hmm? Is there
something not clear?
Zenitsu: No, not that.
You two, come with me.
- Tanjiro: Huh?
- Inosuke: Don't feel like it.
Zenitsu: I won't ask twice!
Shut up, and follow me!
( All gasp )
Zenitsu: Now!
You're coming with me,
you little urchins!
- I got an earful for you!
- ( Tanjiro wails )
Inosuke: What the hell
are you doing?
( Zenitsu shrieks )
All right, you two,
sit up straight!
You miserable bastards!
Inosuke: What did you say to us?
( Babbles )
( Groans )
Tanjiro: Inosuke!
What are you thinking?!
Apologize to Inosuke!
( Inosuke snarling )
Zenitsu: Huh?! Me apologize?!
You're the ones acting
like you came back from hell
when you were in paradise!
All you did was frolic
with girls all day,
so why did you come back
looking all haggard like that?
Apologize! Then drop dead!
Tanjiro: How can you
say such a thing?
Zenitsu: Shut up,
you goody-goody, giant forehead!
Listen to what I have to say!
( Growls )
You get to have beautiful girls
giving you massages!
You touch their hands
during that cup game!
And when you play tag,
you can touch more than that!
All girls have nice chests,
great butts, and strong thighs!
They smell so nice
when they pass by,
and just
getting to look at them
makes my heartbeat quicken!
( Shrieks )
They're heaven,
absolute, utter heaven!
Inosuke: Knock it off!
You're not making any sense!
Isn't getting all shook up
by something smaller than you
a real blow to your confidence?
Zenitsu: That's right! You were
raised in the mountains,
so you've never been
close to a girl, have you?!
No wonder you're a late bloomer!
I feel so sorry for you!
Inosuke: That's it!
I've been close to girls,
and none of them
were a match for me!
Zenitsu: I'm not talking
about fighting!
- Bad, bad, bad!
- ( Girls sigh )
Zenitsu:
You'll never pick up a girl
at this rate!
Inosuke: What do you mean?
There's no way
they can be that heavy!
( Tanjiro groans )
Zenitsu: I look forward
to training with you!
- ( Laughs )
- ( Girls sigh )
- ( Girls grunting )
- ( Zenitsu laughing )
Keep going. This is fine.
Inosuke: I have
underestimated him.
I always fight back tears
from the pain,
but he's laughing from joy.
( Tanjiro groans )
Aoi: I shall take you on.
Girl 2: And go!
Zenitsu: I would never...
Throw a drink in a girl's face.
( Girls groans )
( Zenitsu laughs )
Girl 3: Now then, we will
commence the full-body training!
( Zenitsu yelps ) I win!
- ( Blow smacks )
- I may have won the battle,
but I lost the war.
- Inosuke: I wanna win, too!
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
- Inosuke: All right!
- ( Aoi gasps )
Inosuke: Take this!
- Aoi: Let me down!
- ( Girls sigh )
Tanjiro: I'm the only one
on a losing streak now.
So embarrassing.
- ( Splash )
- ( Both groan )
Tanjiro: But no matter
what I do, I can't beat Kanao.
None of us
can get to our cup first
or block her
from using her own.
For the next five days,
I continued to lose to her.
- ( Inosuke growls )
- Tanjiro: So did Inosuke...
- ( Zenitsu wails )
- Tanjiro: And Zenitsu.
We couldn't so much
as lay a finger
on a strand of her hair.
Then one day,
the other two stopped coming.
Z-Zenitsu? Inosuke?
( Sighs )
Please train me!
( Insects chirping )
Thank you for a good workout.
Why can't I beat her?
What gives her an edge over me?
First of all,
her reflexes are way faster.
I'd probably still lose
at full strength.
Her scent is totally different.
It's similar
to the scent of the hashira.
Girl 3: Tanjiro?
Tanjiro: Also her eyes,
her eyes are different somehow.
Girl 3: Tanjiro?
- 'Scuse me.
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Girl 3: Tanjiro are--
are you all right?
We've been calling to you
over and over.
Tanjiro: Oh! I'm sorry.
What is it?
( Girls sigh )
Girl 1: This is for you.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Thank you! This helps!
You're all so kind!
( Girls sighing )
Girl 1: Um, I wanted
to ask if you keep up
the total concentration
breathing state all of the time.
Tanjiro: Huh?
Girl 1: Do you use
the total concentration
breathing technique nonstop,
morning, noon,
and while you're asleep?
Tanjiro: Uh, can't say I do.
Never thought to.
Can someone pull that off?
Girl 1: Yes! We're told that
being able to do such a thing
makes all the difference
in the whole, wide world!
Tanjiro: Even just
using that technique
for a short period of time
really takes a toll.
But I should do it
around the clock, huh?
Girl 2: Some people have
already been able to master it.
Girl 3: All the hashira
and Kanao, too!
Girls: We hope you can do it!
Tanjiro: Is that so?
Thank you! I'll give it a try.
Tanjiro: I think you should
come back to training, Inosuke.
Feeling sorry for yourself
won't do you any good.
You, too, Zenitsu.
Zenitsu: Well,
those were good times for me.
Tell them
my injury's gotten worse.
Hey, there, Kakushi lady!
Would you like to have
some tea with me?
( Tanjiro groans )
( Breathing deeply )
Total concentration breathing...
Morning, noon, and night.
I said I'd try
to keep it up around the clock.
( Deep breath )
( Groans )
Nope. I can't do it!
Not even close!
If I try to do it
longer than usual,
it makes me feel
like I'm gonna die!
It's too painful.
My lungs hurt!
My ears are ringing so hard,
it feels like
they're gonna burst!
Wait. Did they?
( Wails )
( Gasps )
Ugh. That was so scary!
For a second there,
I thought my heart
had burst out through my ears!
I'll never be able
to do it at this rate.
When you're in trouble,
go back to the basics!
Get it together, me!
( Girls sigh )
( Tanjiro breathing deeply )
Breathing is
all about the lungs.
If I can't grasp it, that means
my lungs are too weak.
( Singers vocalizing )
Work at it!
It's the only thing I can do!
That's how it's always been!
Hard work
is the sum of daily efforts.
It can be one step at a time.
Just move forward!
Move!
Girl 1: Look at him go!
He's working hard, isn't he?
Girl 3: Yeah! Let's bring him
some rice balls, okay?
Girl 3: Good idea! And also...
Tanjiro: Blow into these gourds?
Girl 1: Yeah, that's right!
Lady Kocho trained miss Kanao,
and whenever she did,
she had her blow
into gourds like these.
Tanjiro: Really?
That's a neat
training technique.
So do you make a sound
or something?
Girl 1: Oh, no. She blew into it
and made the gourd
go all ka-boom!
Tanjiro: Wow!
Ka-boom?
Wait. This thing, explode?
( Taps gourd )
Something this hard?
Girl 1: That's right!
Not to mention,
this is a special kind of gourd,
so it's even harder
than normal ones.
Tanjiro: A girl that delicate
was able to pull off
something like that?!
Girl 1: Did I mention the gourds
get bigger and bigger
as you progress?
The one that lady Kanao
is able to explode right now...
Is this one right here.
Tanjiro: It's huge!
I'll give it a shot!
Aoi: They're not
coming today, either?
Tanjiro: 'Fraid not.
I'll bring them tomorrow.
Sorry.
Aoi: It's fine.
Don't concern yourself
with those two anymore!
Tanjiro: I'll do my best.
Here I go!
( Grunts )
I've been running
Urokodaki's drills
while maintaining my total
concentration breathing.
( Grunting )
While racing around here,
I imagine
I'm at the mountains back home.
And instead of these obstacles,
they're the trees
I used to avoid.
( Growls ) Keep at it!
Keep at it! Keep at it!
I've regained
most of my stamina,
and now I can run farther
than I did before,
and my lungs
are getting stronger, too!
- This is good.
- ( Breathing deeply )
During the day,
I cover a lot of distance
and put my lungs
into overdrive.
And now I'll take
slow, deep breaths
and imagine sending that air
all the way to my fingertips.
Meditation boosts concentration.
Urokodaki said so himself.
Urokodaki.
Haganezuka: I can't believe
you'd go
and break my sword like that!
Tanjiro: I'm so sorry.
They're reforging
my sword for me now,
but I still
feel terrible about it.
Now's not the time
to be thinking about that!
Concentrate on your breathing!
Shinobu: Yoo-hoo! Hello!
Yoo-hoo! Hello.
Tanjiro: Yes?!
Shinobu: Working hard, I see.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Shinobu: Even though
your friends
didn't end up joining you.
( Tanjiro shudders )
Shinobu: Aren't you lonely
all by yourself?
Tanjiro: No way!
Once I've mastered it,
I can teach it to them myself!
Shinobu: You have
a beautiful soul, don't you?
Tanjiro: Uh...
( Sighs )
So, uh, why did you decide
to bring us all here
in the first place?
Shinobu: Nezuko's presence
is no longer considered taboo,
and the three of you
had been terribly injured.
Additionally, if I could,
I'd like to entrust
a dream of mine to you.
Tanjiro: A dream?
Shinobu: Yes.
That we can befriend
the demons.
I'm sure
you can accomplish that.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Sniffs )
Are you angry?
( Shinobu gasps )
Tanjiro: For some reason,
I always pick up
a scent of anger,
even though
you're always smiling.
Shinobu: Yes. You are correct.
It may be
that I'm constantly angry.
My beloved older sister
was slaughtered by a demon.
I see
the mournful tears of others
who've lost their loved ones
in the same way.
I hear
their loud cries of despair,
and each time I do,
the anguish inside me
grows larger.
In the innermost depths
of my soul,
there's a hatred
that I can't fight.
I'm sure the other hashira
feel something similar.
But now, with their own eyes,
they've seen a demon
who's never devoured a human.
They can't deny her existence.
Due to the master's wishes,
I don't believe anyone
will raise a hand to Nezuko.
( Tanjiro sighs )
( Singers vocalizing )
Shinobu: My sister was
a kindhearted person like you.
She had sympathy for demons.
Even when she was on the brink
of death, that didn't change.
I couldn't bring myself
to feel that way.
To do so
for something that's killed us?
I'd never heard
of such nonsense.
But if that was
how my sister truly felt,
- then I must carry it on.
- ( Sobbing )
If there is a way not to kill
these pitiful demons,
I have to keep trying to find it
while keeping the smile
my sister said she loved.
Sister!
No!
Stay with me!
I have to admit
I'm rather tired.
Demons do nothing but lie.
They only fight to survive,
murdering us,
and do so
without any shred of humanity.
¶
Tanjiro, please do all you can.
Protect your sister
until the end.
Knowing that you're working hard
to carry out what I could not,
it warms my heart.
I can rest easy now.
( Wind blows )
( Tanjiro sighs )
Shinobu: You've stopped your
total concentration breathing.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Shinobu giggles )
Tanjiro: Focus.
Total concentration breathing.
¶
Mother, Hanako...
Takeo, Shigeru...
Rokuta...
( Groans )
I will turn Nezuko
back into a human!
( Singers vocalizing )
¶
( singing in Japanese )