Swordsman:
Hope you're ready for me,
'cause I'm comin' through!
Demon: It's all so infuriating!
( Drum beats )
( Swordsman gasps )
( Teruko yelps )
Tanjiro: Teruko!
Hold on to the furniture!
( Grunts )
That demon has special powers!
You shouldn't be attacking
so recklessly!
( Swordsman laughs )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( rumbling )
( Swordsman grunts )
Demon: How maddening,
all these cursed insects
running amok in my house.
( Beats drum twice )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
- ( Rumbles )
- ( Teruko gasps )
- ( Swordsman growls )
( Teruko grunting )
( Swordsman laughing )
I can't believe
the room spun around!
Now, this is
what I call a fun time!
( Laughs )
Tanjiro: Get your dirty feet
off of her!
Swordsman:
Who the hell are you, kid?
Tanjiro: Stepping
on a little kid like that!
What are you thinking?!
( Swordsman laughs )
You got spunk. I like that.
Having a human send me flying,
that's a first for me!
( Yells )
Tanjiro: Why is he
coming after me?
Isn't he a demon slayer?
Swordsman: These swords
do a lot of damage.
They're not the kind
you delicate little flowers
would use.
The way they shred through flesh
is what I pride myself on
the most.
Tanjiro: This is foolish!
There's a demon right there!
Swordsman:
You think I care?! Hah!
Demon: Measly insects.
You're irksome.
Now die!
( Tanjiro gasps )
The floor just ripped apart.
It happened at the speed
of the beat of the drum
and in the shape
of a beast's claws!
Rotating right.
Back left.
Demon: Insects.
Miserable vermin!
( Swordsman groans )
Tanjiro: I'm starting
to understand.
( Demon muttering )
( Drum beating )
Tanjiro:
We're in another room now?
But that demon
didn't strike his drum,
so what does this mean?
I'm picking up the scent of
multiple demons in this house.
Is there another demon
with a drum, then?
Is that why...
( Sniffs )
( Teruko whimpering )
Tanjiro: I can smell blood.
It's gonna be fine.
You just stay behind me.
( Teruko grunts )
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
another human mauled and eaten.
Teruko: Is something wrong?
Tanjiro: No, we're fine.
There's no demons.
Come on. Let's head out.
Keep your eyes forward,
all right?
Don't look behind you.
( Sniffs )
I smell something else,
a unique scent of blood
that I've never smelled before.
Seems like
there wasn't much bleeding.
¶
( teruko grunts )
( Boy gasps )
( Footsteps scraping )
( Zenitsu panting )
( Shoichi grunts )
Excuse me.
Can we stop, zenitsu?
( Zenitsu shrieks )
( Wailing )
You gotta warn me first
before you speak up!
You can't go surprising me
like that here!
My heart nearly jumped
out of my mouth just now!
Shoichi: Sorry about that.
Zenitsu: If I had
a heart attack,
you would have been
directly responsible!
You'd be a murderer!
Do you understand?!
Shoichi: Well, it's just that...
You've been sweating, gasping,
and shivering really badly.
Zenitsu: What about it?!
I'm doing the best
I can here, all right?!
Shoichi: Um,
forgive me for saying so,
but you're making me
really nervous, too.
Zenitsu: Oh, no! I'm sorry!
It's just I feel if we
make too much noise here,
that demon you saw,
it might find us, right?
That's why
I think it would be best
to be as quiet as possible!
Don't you think?!
( Scraping )
( Shoichi gasps )
( Zenitsu shuddering )
( Demon laughs )
A couple of kids.
I bet you'll taste delicious.
Zenitsu: What did I tell you?!
It's just my luck
we'd run into a demon!
)
Stay away! Stay away from us!
I'm warning you!
( Demon growling )
( Laughs )
Zenitsu: W-we don't taste good!
I'm sure I taste awful!
I'm serious!
This kid's all skin and bones,
so he'd be dry
and taste terrible!
( Demon laughs )
How will I know for sure
until I have a lick?
( Zenitsu shrieks )
Are you kidding me?!
His tongue is like
a bolt of lighting!
( Demon growls )
Zenitsu: This has
to be a nightmare!
( Wails )
( Shoichi gasps )
Zenitsu, you've gotta get up!
( Zenitsu wails ) My knees!
My fear is in my knees!
Shoichi: This isn't the time
to complain about that stuff!
( Zenitsu groans )
Just leave me behind, okay?
Make a run for it!
Shoichi: I can't
do something like that.
( Zenitsu shrieks )
What a sweet kid.
As useless as I am,
he's sticking by me.
I gotta find
a solution to this.
If I don't protect him, I don't
wanna think of what'll happen.
Dying before he reaches
adulthood would be tragic.
But I'm so horribly weak.
Shoichi: Get up!
Zenitsu: I don't have
the strength to protect him.
But, if I don't,
then that would mean...
( Demon laughs )
I'm going to relish
using my tongue
to scoop your brains
out through your ears.
( Zenitsu snorts )
( Gasps )
Shoichi: Zenitsu!
Are you...
( Gasps )
( Zenitsu snoring )
Shoichi: He's asleep.
( Demon laughs )
What's up with him?
( Shoichi grunting )
( Demon laughing )
( Shoichi gasping )
( Demon grunts ) Die!
( Shoichi yells )
Please wake up!
Zenitsu!
¶
( slice )
( Demon groans )
( Shoichi grunts )
¶
( chorus vocalizing )
Demon: Eh?
( Growls )
( Zenitsu exhales )
Demon: Wh-what is this sound?
This boy,
he's not the same as before.
Shoichi: Zenitsu?
Zenitsu: Thunder breathing...
First form.
Thunderclap and flash.
( Demon gasps )
( Shoichi gasps )
( Zenitsu snorts )
( Gasps )
( Shrieks )
It's dead?!
When did that happen?!
What the hell?! This is weird!
What is this? Yuck!
( Gasps )
Shoichi, did--did you just...
( Gasps ) You saved me!
Thank you so much!
I'll never forget
that you did this!
Why didn't you
just tell me from the start
that you were so powerful?!
- ( Sobbing )
- Shoichi: Huh?
What are you talking about?
Zenitsu: You say something?
Shoichi: Huh? No.
Uh, mm-mmm.
It's nothing.
We should go now.
Zenitsu: Yeah.
( Swordsman panting )
Damn it!
He sent me flying again!
These last three days,
it's been the same old crap.
I don't like making my way
through a cramped building
like this!
It's just not my thing
( growling )
( Demon growls )
Swordsman: Huh?
Demon: You dodged that.
You seem quite spry, human.
Your healthy flesh will be
well worth gouging out to eat!
( Swordsman growls )
( Exhales )
Self-taught style,
beast breathing!
It's gonna feel so good to rip
such a huge target to shreds!
( Demon laughs )
You've got a lot of guts
to charge me head-on like that!
( Groans )
( Wailing )
( Swordsman laughs )
Revel in your own death,
and serve as my catalyst!
( Demon gags )
Swordsman: Fang three, devour!
¶
( swordsman laughs )
Coming through! Coming through!
( Footsteps rumbling )
Demon: Marechi, I need it.
To devour even one,
I would have as many as 50--
nay, 100 bodies worth.
I must search for more humans
with marechi and devour them.
In doing so, I will be able
to reclaim my place
among the twelve kizuki.
( Demon gobbling )
Kibutsuji: Kyogai.
( Kyogai grunts )
Kibutsuji:
Why have you stopped eating?
( Kyogai gasps )
Kibutsuji: Have you
reached your limit?
Kyogai: No, sir. I can go on!
( Groans )
P-Please! Give me
just a little more time.
Kibutsuji: I think not.
I am stripping you
of your number,
because you have
nothing more to offer me.
Kyogai:
The more humans you devour,
the stronger you become.
Once he saw my potential,
master kibutsuji was willing
to share his blood with me.
The power of that man's blood
was simply astonishing.
I was sure that I'd grow
infinitely stronger
than ever before
and recognized into the ranks
of the twelve kizuki.
I would continue
to gorge myself on humans
and steadily become
even more powerful!
Or so I believed.
( Teruko gasps )
Kiyoshi, we found you!
( Kiyoshi gasps )
Teruko: Brother! Brother!
Kiyoshi: Teruko!
Who is he?
Tanjiro: Tanjiro kamado,
and I'm a demon slayer.
( Kiyoshi gasps )
Tanjiro: You two have
hung in there really well.
Can you show me your wounds?
( Kiyoshi sobs )
Teruko: Why, Kiyoshi?
¶
tanjiro: This ointment here
is really amazing!
My master gave it to me
for a time like this!
Wanna know something funny?
He always wears a tengu mask.
Kiyoshi: A tengu? Really?
Tanjiro: It's the truth.
Anyway, this ointment
is fantastic.
You'll feel better right away.
That'll do it!
Well? You feel better?
Kiyoshi: Yes.
Tanjiro: Tell me exactly
what happened if you can.
( Kiyoshi gasping )
A monster dragged me away,
and...
It nearly ate me.
Mm, but then...
Another one showed up
out of nowhere.
They started
fighting to the death over...
Who was gonna get to e-eat me.
Then...
The demon with the drums
growing out of him...
Left one of the drums behind
after he was defeated
by the others.
When I picked it up and hit it,
the room changed.
That's how I held out.
( Sobbing )
Tanjiro: A demon with drums
growing from him? That guy?
He said, I think,
something about "marechi."
( Kiyoshi gasps )
Yes, that's right!
I don't know what it means,
but he called me that!
( Crow caws )
The term "marechi"
refers to the owner
of a rare type of blood!
( Both gasp )
( Crow laughs )
What's that look?
I'll teach you respect!
Tanjiro: Cut it out!
When you say, "rare blood,"
wh-what do you mean?
Crow: The blood
of all living species
can be broken into types,
you see?
The more scarce the blood--
or the more uncommon it is,
I should say--
the more desirable
it is to demons,
for, you see, in terms of
nutritional value for a demon,
a human marechi is akin
to eating as many
as a hundred normal humans.
A marechi is like
a bountiful feast for them,
a delicacy for the ages.
( Both shuddering )
( Tanjiro sniffs )
( Gasps )
¶
marechi. Marechi.
( Tanjiro groans )
I'm gonna head out there.
( Kiyoshi gasps )
Tanjiro: Keep calm.
It's all right.
I'm going
to take down that demon.
- Teruko, listen to me.
- Teruko: Huh?
Your brother is really worn out
at the moment,
so watch after him, all right?
( Teruko grunts )
Tanjiro: Soon as
I leave this room,
use the drum to change areas,
just like Kiyoshi's been doing.
If someone tries to open
the door or you hear something,
strike that drum
to remove yourself from danger.
I promise
that I'll come for you.
I'll follow your scent back.
Then I'll call your names
so you know it's me.
( Both whimper )
Tanjiro: Just hold out
a little longer.
Can you do it?
( Both grunt )
Great! So brave!
I'm off.
( Footsteps pounding )
¶
( chorus vocalizing )
Strike it!
( Beats drum )
Kyogai: Damn insects.
So infuriating!
¶
( tanjiro gasps )
The right drum
flips the room right.
The left one flips it left.
Right leg, forward spin!
Left leg, backward spin!
The drum on his belly
launches that claw attack!
( Pounding drums )
¶
( Gasps )
So fast.
The speed of the rotations
and attacks are brutal!
Miss tamayo did treat my wounds,
but these injuries
aren't fully healed yet.
Can i--can I beat him?
I'm in so much pain.
I don't know how much longer
I can hold on!
This whole time,
I've just been grinning
and bearing it.
When I pulled zenitsu
off that girl he was chasing,
when I shouted at him
out of anger,
I was enduring
the most terrible pain.
I had to withstand it.
It was my duty
as the eldest son of my family.
Whenever I tense up,
my broken bones ache,
stopping me
from mustering any strength.
That demon's attack
is leaving tears
that look like claw marks.
I'm too scared
to move in closer.
If I charge forward
to get within striking distance,
I'm afraid that a flash of pain
will make me falter.
If that happens...
I'll be torn to shreds.
I can't help but imagine
the most awful things.
Help me!
Urokodaki: Consider
the characteristics of water.
Pour it into a container,
and it's square.
Pour it into a bottle,
and it's round.
It can smash boulders or
flow as far as the eye can see.
Tanjiro: Of course.
That's right!
I remember. There are
ten water breathing forms,
so I can adapt to any opponent.
If you're wounded,
then you have to make a move
that will compensate for it.
I can take on any form, and
this flow will never be stopped!
More important than my bones,
my spirit was broken.
( Zenitsu weeps )
That's not gonna
do anyone any good!
Tanjiro: Would you stay
out of my head, please?!
Look straight ahead.
Steel yourself.
Give it everything you've got.
You can do it!
¶
I've been able
to survive this long.
I know I have what it takes!
Whether it's today or tomorrow,
I can assure you this!
( Kyogai growls )
Tanjiro: Without a shadow
of doubt in my mind,
I will not yield!
¶
( singing in Japanese )