Tanjiro: The twelve kizuki
should possess
a high amount
of Kibutsuji's blood.
If I can extract it,
the medicine that'll help
Nezuko will be finished sooner.
( Gasps )
Inosuke's still back there.
Inosuke: So did you
take out that monster?
Tanjiro: Hey, are you okay?
You're bleeding.
Inosuke: I asked you if you
defeated that thing or not!
Tanjiro: Uh, yeah, I did!
But enough about that.
Your wounds--
Inosuke: Don't go showering me
with your mushy sensitivity
and kindness!
I don't need it. You got that?
After all, anything you can do,
I can do, too!
Before you know it,
my head will be--
my head will be
even harder than yours.
Not to mention that--
not to mention--
not to mention...
Tanjiro: He's not doing well.
And I couldn't save
our other friends, either.
That woman gave off a scent
of terror and suffering...
¶
enough to make her
yearn for death.
What is it
about this mountain, anyway?
- A Demon family living here...
- Hey, stay still, Inosuke.
As well as one
of the twelve kizuki?
Inosuke: Cut it out!
I'm totally fine, all right?
Tanjiro: I didn't think demons
gathered together like that.
Zenitsu: Ouch!
Ow!
Something just pricked me.
What the hell?
I'm so frustrated.
I can't find Tanjiro
or Inosuke anywhere!
Where did they go?
Great! Now what?
Something really stinks
around here, too! Gross!
( Chuntaro squeals )
Zenitsu: I think I'm gonna cry.
And the sound of these spiders
running around is so creepy.
I'm sure they're just doing
their best to survive,
the same as me, but still!
Be quiet! Stop moving around!
¶
what am I even looking at?!
( Singing in Japanese )
¶
( Zenitsu shrieks )
Why did that spider
have a human face on it?!
What is happening right now?!
What is happening?!
Please be a dream!
If I wake up right now,
I promise to work harder!
If I were to wake up
in the presence
of my precious Nezuko,
then I'll do anything!
I'll do hard manual labor.
I'll even plow fields,
a whole acre, no, two!
I promise!
Let me wake up
from this nightmare!
( Gasping )
( Victim groaning )
Zenitsu: The heck is that?
Are those humans
who got turned into spiders?
Is that house floating?
I can't quite make it out,
but are those threads?
And it really stinks!
Talk about pungent!
Tanjiro would hate this
for sure!
The smell
is making my throat hurt!
Not just that.
It's irritating my eyes, too,
( wood creaking )
( Zenitsu shrieks )
( Brother growls )
Zenitsu: It's huge!
Look at the size of that thing!
It's absolutely gigantic!
( Brother laughs )
( Zenitsu whimpering )
You better
not start talking to me!
I don't wanna hear it from you!
( Groans )
( Brother laughs )
There's no point
in running away!
You've already lost the battle!
Zenitsu: I told you
not to talk to me!
I don't wanna hear it,
so stop talking!
Things like you
give me the creeps, all right?
Brother: So you already know
how dire
the situation is for you.
Zenitsu: What are
you talking about?
Brother: Hah!
Take a look at your hands.
Zenitsu: My hands? Why?
( Brother laughs )
Zenitsu:
What's wrong with my ha--
( gasps )
What's this?
Brother: You're poisoned.
A spider bit you, didn't it?
You're gonna
turn into one before long.
( Laughs )
( Zenitsu whimpering )
Brother: In half an hour,
you'll be my slave,
crawling all over the ground!
( Laughs )
Do you understand?
Here. I'll use
this watch to explain.
By the time this long hand
goes around once,
you'll have become
one of the spiders.
- When the hand arrives here...
- ( Watch ticking )
You'll feel tingling
and pain in your limbs.
When it's here,
you'll feel dizzy and nauseous.
Here, your body
will painfully start to shrink,
and you'll black out.
And by the time you wake up...
( Laughs )
( Women vocalizing )
( Zenitsu groans )
( Watch ticking )
( Screams )
Huh?
( Creatures grunting )
( Zenitsu screaming )
( Brother laughs )
- Running away--
- Zenitsu: Is useless! I know!
But you're crazy if you think
I'm not gonna try and get away!
( Grunting )
( Brother laughs )
What do you think you're doing?
Zenitsu: Shut up! Shut up!
Just you shut up!
Brother: There's no need
to be afraid.
Once the transformation
has taken effect,
- you'll lose your humanity.
- Zenitsu: Exactly!
That's just what I've
been dreading about all this!
Why can't you get that
through your head, huh?!
Someone like you wouldn't have
anyone special in their lives!
( Brother growls ) Maybe
some more poison would help
so we can speed up
the process for you.
( Zenitsu wails )
( Brother chuckles )
( Zenitsu screams )
No, not that!
Stay away from me!
I don't want to turn into
one of those things!
( Whimpers )
Man: Get ahold of yourself!
Stop crying and running away!
Doing that isn't going
to get you anywhere!
Come down from there!
You hear me, Zenitsu?
We're going
to continue training!
Zenitsu: If I go through
another one
of your training regimens,
I'm gonna die!
I'm not gonna
be able to handle it!
Man: You're not going to die,
not from this!
Come down from there, you fool!
Zenitsu: Come on, gramps!
Grandfather:
Address me as "master"!
Zenitsu: But I wanna call
you gramps, 'cause I love you!
( Grandfather groaning )
Zenitsu: When the girl I loved
made me raise money
so she could run off
with another guy,
you rescued me
from my mountain of debt!
Maybe all you wanted was
to be able to train a swordsman,
but I want to live up
to your expectations, too!
I don't know that I can, though.
I feel terrible about the fact
that I'm like this.
I really do! Just so you know,
I've been skipping out on sleep
so that I can train more,
but I have absolutely
nothing to show for it!
Why?! Seriously, is there
some reason I don't know about?!
Grandfather:
Calm yourself, Zenitsu!
- The potential lies within you!
- ( Thunder rumbling )
Zenitsu:
I've had enough of it all!
Grandfather: Zenitsu,
are you okay?!
Zenitsu: Getting hit
by lighting...
How unlucky can you get?
That's when
my hair color changed.
I was thankful just to be alive,
but even so...
I-I hate myself
more than anyone else.
I always try
to get my act together,
but I just end up running away
or cowering in fear.
I'm pathetic.
I want to change. I want
to be a capable individual.
The fact is...
I'm doing absolutely
everything that I can!
But I still
have to be turned into
some horrific spider creature?!
It can't be! Say it isn't true!
( Sobbing )
Brother: What's up
with this guy?
He's a strange one.
¶
( Zenitsu whimpers )
Oh, crap! Don't climb up here!
Can't you leave me alone
for just a little bit?!
This is all too much
for me to handle right now!
Eh? Huh?
My hair's falling out already?
Wait. My hair.
Hey, he never mentioned
that part to me!
( Whimpers )
( Brother chuckles )
( Zenitsu groans )
Brother: Huh?
I don't understand
this guy at all.
Isn't he a Demon slayer who
came here to kill our family?
But he fainted.
How spineless can you get?
He's gonna fall on his head
and die.
What the hell?
( Zenitsu exhales )
Thunder breathing technique.
First form...
Brother: Huh?
Poison sputum!
( Sputum sizzles )
Did he just
twist his body in midair?
With such quick reflexes,
I hardly recognize him.
¶
thunder breathing. First form...
Brother: Hey, you guys,
go take him down!
Zenitsu: Thunder breathing,
first form...
( Brother grunts )
He's been going into
that same stance over and over.
( Chuckles )
Ah, I know why he's doing that.
He must only be capable
of that one attack.
Grandfather:
Don't worry about it, Zenitsu.
That's good enough progress.
Mastering even one
is cause for celebration.
If you can only do one thing,
hone it to perfection.
Work on refining it
to its utmost potential.
Zenitsu: But, gramps,
just a little while ago,
you were really angry,
because thunder breathing
has six forms,
and all I can manage to do
is one.
Grandfather:
Do you know what the process
of forging a sword is?
Zenitsu: I don't know.
I wish he'd stop hitting me.
I'm gonna cry.
Grandfather:
When making a sword,
you hammer and hammer
to get rid of impurities
and anything else
you don't need.
The greater
the purity of the blade,
the more durable it becomes.
Zenitsu: Is that
why you keep clobbering me
day in and day out?
But I'm not made of steel.
I'm living flesh.
( Brother chuckles )
You're not much
of a threat, are you?
And you call yourself
a Demon slayer?
Any minute now,
you'll be rendered immobile
by that poison.
Grandfather:
Zenitsu, perfect it!
It's all right to cry
or go off by yourself.
Just don't ever give up.
Believe in yourself.
You endured
all that hellish training.
You'll be rewarded for that
without question.
Work to forge yourself
like a tempered blade
and become
the most resilient of all!
Focus on what you do best!
¶
Man: Get out of here.
Zenitsu: Huh?
Man: You gonna
make me repeat myself?
Leave my sight.
You know why.
The way you cry
like a baby all day long,
aren't you ashamed of yourself?
( Zenitsu sighs )
( Man scoffs ) Good for nothing.
Any effort spent on you
is an absolute waste of time.
Our teacher
is an extraordinary man.
Zenitsu:
But gramps told me that--
- ( gasps )
- Man: Hey, you,
don't go being all familiar
and calling him "gramps"!
He's a former hashira,
someone who earned
the highest title
in the Demon slayer corps!
Hardly anyone
ever gets the chance
to be trained
by a former hashira.
The time he spends training you
is all for nothing.
It's infuriating to see!
I hate even looking at you,
so get out!
Why are you even here?
Why do you insist on clinging on
like a patch of mold?!
¶
Zenitsu: I have no parents,
no one who has hopes for me,
no one with dreams
that eventually, one day,
I'll be able to accomplish
something important...
Not even a thing as simple
as proving myself
useful to someone,
either by protecting them
or making them happy,
just once in my life.
I have no one like that.
If you mess up or cry
or run away even once,
everyone says, "oh, this guy's
no good," and walk away.
Or so I thought.
( Gagging )
( Grandfather grunting )
Zenitsu: Time and time again,
gramps would run me
through my paces.
I tried running away
on numerous occasions.
- But each time I did...
- ( Yelps )
He'd drag me right back.
( Grandfather chuckles )
Zenitsu: He smacked me around
a little too much for my liking,
but he never abandoned me.
Brother: Get him!
Inject more poison
into his veins!
( Zenitsu gags )
( Women vocalizing )
( Brother laughs )
That should do it.
( Energy crackles )
Brother: Eh?
What's this?
The air is vibrating.
( Zenitsu grunts )
( Brother gasps )
Zenitsu: Thunder breathing.
First form,
thunderclap and flash!
( Brother gasps )
Zenitsu: Sixfold!
( Brother grunts )
( Gasps ) He vanished?
¶
( chorus vocalizing )
( Gagging )
Did I get slashed? Me?
It can't be!
To think, by someone like him.
( Groans )
This is ridiculous!
I was defeated by someone who
could hardly move their limbs!
( Groans )
( Ticking )
( Zenitsu coughs )
I just wanna dream
a happy, peaceful dream.
In it, I'm more powerful
than anyone.
I'm able to help the weak,
anyone in trouble anytime...
And everything
that gramps taught me,
all the time and
effort he spent,
it wasn't for nothing.
In this dream, thanks to gramps,
I became strong and was able
to help a lot of people.
But the time for dreams
is over now.
( Bird trilling )
( Chuntaro chirps )
Zenitsu:
Is that you, Chuntaro?
( Chuntaro chirps )
Zenitsu: I'm so sorry.
( Squeals )
( Zenitsu sighs )
Grandfather:
Don't ever give up!
¶
( Zenitsu inhales )
"don't ever give up."
I can use
the breathing technique
to slow down the poison.
Even if it's painful,
even if it's agonizing,
don't try to take
the easy way out,
or gramps will let you have it.
Yeah, and Tanjiro's
gonna yell at you, too.
( Thunder crashes )
Tanjiro: What was that sound?
Did lightning just strike?
Inosuke: How should I know?
Tanjiro: Well, I'm not
smelling any thunderclouds,
but that odor got stronger
and is messing
with my senses again.
Inosuke!
Inosuke: What? ( Grunts )
Tanjiro: I think I'm gonna
go take that path instead.
Inosuke: Why are you telling me?
Do whatever you want!
Tanjiro: So are you
headed back down?
Inosuke: Back down?
Tanjiro:
Down the mountain, I mean.
Inosuke: Why would I do that?
Just beat it!
Tanjiro: What about
all your wounds, though?
Inosuke: What are you
talking about?!
I'm not hurt at all!
( Bell clangs )
Tanjiro: What?
You've gotta be kidding,
Inosuke.
Anyone from a mile away
could see how bloodied you are.
( Footsteps approaching )
- Eh?
- Inosuke: Huh?
¶
( Demon gasps )
Tanjiro: A Demon!
The scent hanging
over this mountain
blocked me from picking that up!
( Inosuke roars )
Listen up, you damn Demon!
I'm gonna tear you to shreds!
Get back here!
Tanjiro: Hang on!
Demon: Now, father!
Inosuke:
Who are you callin' "father"?
( Gasps )
Tanjiro: Inosuke!
( Father growls )
( Roars )
( Both gasp )
Father: Don't you
come near my family!
Stay away from them!
Sister: I'm leaving
the rest to you...
Father.
( Inosuke groans )
( Father growls )
Tanjiro: Water breathing.
Second form,
water wheel!
( Yelling )
¶
( Singing in Japanese )