[ALL]
Eeee...
What am I looking at?
That's one blunt sword!
[BOY]
That transfer student is up to
his weird tricks again.
[OTHER BOY]
Is he trying to
throw this thing?!
I understand now, must be
why you didn't bother
coming out to the market
this morning, Soma.
[SOMA] Huh?!
You chose to age your fish
to make up for the difference
in quality that your
fish would lack.
Nice try, but I could
tell what you used
the second I looked at your
pathetic little fish...
It won't be enough.
You're not going to match a
fresh, seasonal ingredient.
[SOMA]
Yeah well you can't really know
that without eatin' it, can ya?
But don't worry, I made enough
for you guys to try as well.
You can talk all you want,
the competitions been decided.
Congratulations...
coming in third.
That's still plenty
to be proud of.
[SOMA]
Hm.
[SATOSHI]
Ladies and gentlemen...
It seems the time
has finally arrived.
Let the finals of the
Fall Selection begin.
Turn your attention
to the ceiling.
[CROWD]
Ohhhh...
[STUDENT]
So awesome!
[BOY]
The friggin' ceiling
just opened up man!
Very soon now...
Everyone, we shall witness
the Celestial Room's true form.
[CROWD]
Ohhhh!
[SATOSHI]
Cooking time for the competition
will be two hours.
It will last from when
the moon peers upon us...
to when it disappears from view.
It will be a night of
cooking under the stars.
[GIN]
This may be an annual custom,
but it's quite majestic,
isn't it?
It brings me back
to those nostalgic days.
Back to that magical night
when I had to fight
in my own Selection.
All the chefs that have
stood on this same stage
have all gazed in awe
upon this moon.
Don't go losing to anyone,
until you've lost to me again.
[SOMA]
This is mine!
I will be taking the top seat.
[SENZAEMON]
Prepare yourselves!
LET THE COOKING BEGIN!
[GIN]
This is interesting...
none of the contestants have
reached for their saury.
They're continuing to prep
their other ingredients.
Playing by the book, huh?
They seem to know that
needless handling can lead to
a decrease in freshness.
Not wanting to ruin it,
they must retain as much of
that freshness as possible.
Hehe...
I find I am becoming
quite excited in here.
There is no better sight than
watching such handsome young men
playing with their swords, yes!
Goodness, Mother, that was
extremely lewd of you!
And as always,
your vocab is a bit off.
Alice! Go back to your
stupid seat already!
You should come over
here too, Erina.
Um, it's okay,
right, Grandfather?
Yes, I care not.
See? What did I
tell ya, Erina?
Haha... You can't say you're
family isn't fun, Erina.
What's this?
It seems Soma Yukihira is
the first to grab his fish.
I wonder if he's managed
to age it properly.
Yeah, and what kind of dish
is he going to make with it?
Ryo Kurokiba and Akira Hayama,
Will you be able to beat
those two monsters, Soma?
[OIZUMI]
Oh! Young Ryo has assorted
seafood at his cooking station!
And I see he added
ripe tomatoes and
olive oil as well!
This should be delicious.
He probably intends to make
an acqua pazza.
[GIN]
Acqua pazza, a popular
rustic dish reigning
from southern Italy.
The star ingredient is fish,
which is simmered with
various ingredients.
It's a dish that is simple
yet luxurious.
It common knowledge to add
the olive oil, tomato,
and shellfish to dish like this.
A key feature is that
it doesn't have much
seasoning added to it.
By him simplifying this,
he's able to highlight the
quality of the ingredients.
It's the perfect dish
to make use of his eye
for freshness.
[OIZUMI]
Still, all those ingredients
can play starring roles
on their own.
I'm not quite sure
what he's trying to do.
Simmering the saury with those
will muddle the flavor.
That's a good point.
That seasonal saury would be...
Ah! Seasonal!
[GIN]
That seems to be the key.
Rather than becoming
muddled and lost,
seasonal saury has
the potential to be
the star of the entire dish.
There's no doubt
why he chose this.
He's showing how confident
he is in his trained eye.
As you can see,
he's very calm...
There's not a trace of
pressure on his face.
He's in his element.
Very impressive.
That's just him in
his natural state.
[GIN] Huh?
The two of us have been fighting
in serious culinary battles
for years now!
Hehe...
That does take me back.
You two were so cute
when you were young and
rebellious in fighting, yes.
I didn't know you
knew him while he was
in living in Europe...
Well, Auntie Leonora?
You dare call me "Auntie"?!
How rude!
You are selfish to
brag about your own
pretty girl youth,
you miserable creature
of ageless vim and vigor!
Oh whatever! I didn't call you
"granny," I said "Auntie".
So just simmer down.
You really think such
of this boy, Alice?
Yes, I do Mother!
I'm thinking of making him
my personal attendant!
Let go of me
you white viper.
Erina gets to have
her own secretary.
So I want my own attendant
who's my age too!
(Dog barks and growls)
Yes, well, we must ask your
father about this dear.
Don't get ahead
of yourselves!
I own the top spot in
this restaurant, honey.
I have no intention
of serving unde‐
I believe I told you
to address me properly,
mind your manners servant.
[RYO] Just leave!
Well then, how about we
have a cooking battle?
[RYO] What?
If you lose, you'll become
my loyal puppy dog forever.
Woof, woof, woof!
(Ryo roars)
That girl's dish there
is much tastier. Sorry.
(Ryo groans)
[ALICE] Well then...
Time to get on all fours
and bark for me.
Argh! I challenge you to
another BATTTLE! RIGHT NOW!
(Music plays)
Tee‐hee hee‐hee.
(Crowd cheers)
AAHHHH!
[RYO]
Two years after our
very first battle...
it finally happened...
I WON for the first time.
[COOK 2] Way to go chef! Yeah!
[COOK 3]Victory is yours Master!
(Cooks cheer)
Hmf! I'm challenging you
again tomorrow!
You got that,
you're going down!
[RYO]
Sure thing, Miss Alice.
Huh?
Mark my words...
I'll fight as long
as you want.
(Giggle)
(People laughing)
If I win next time,
you have to speak to me
more politely. Okay?
Don't push it, honey!
[SOMA] Oh?
[ AKIRA] Huh?
[AKIRA]
Heat‐resistant film?
[SOMA]
Ooh. That isn't
regular plastic wrap.
[ZENJI]
This type of film is
able to resist temperatures
from minus 40 degrees
to almost 400.
It's a special film that
lets you cook food while
it's still wrapped.
[ERINA]
It smacks of
molecular gastronomy...
something he surely must have
picked up from Alice.
The dishes he makes now would
have never occurred to him
if it hadn't been for Alice
and her new methods.
She showed him
all these techniques.
It's a reflection of
their history.
Their shared competitions.
[ALICE]
I'm counting on you Ryo...
Do it.
[RYO]
That goes without saying,
Miss Alice.
I've got this...
This touch will be key...
it will add everything
to my dish!
Akira! I'm gonna use this
to finally finish you off!
Only one chef will reach
the top of the Selection...
and that Chef is ME!
[MEGUMI]
Hey look, the moon's gone
halfway across the sky.
So that's leaves just
one more hour left.
Ah, look at that.
Now it's ready.
It looks like Ryo is
the first one done.
But could you really call it...
...a real dish?
You finished quite fast, Ryo.
Here's hoping you didn't
overlook anything
in the process.
You just keep on talking crap
while you still can, spice boy.
My dish is going to slay
anything you think you've got!
[SOMA]
What the heck is that Ryo up to?
And what's that thin film he's
got wrapped around everything?
You'll see, it's something
you're probably familiar with.
[SOMA]
Huh?
And Ryo Kurokiba is the
first contestant to serve.
[GIN]
As the competitor
approaches the judges'...
the Moon offers
a shimmering glow...
Reigning down...
soaking both the chef
and his dish...
as if being purified
by the night.
Pleasure!
I find it is still bubbling
inside of bag, yes.
It is very hot and
steamy, please.
He's serving it as is
and making the judges
do the work themselves?
Very well!
Let's get to tasting!
(Gasp)
Ohhh!
[GIN]
Shrimp, mussels, clams,
and of course, the SAURY!
I'm being swallowed by the
billowing waves of aroma!
[LEONORA]
Oh! The tension is
draining from my face
to a new found glow!
[OIZUMI]
Oh! The director!
Even our austere director
is grinning a glorious grin!
[SAOTOME]
It's a real grin!
I never imagined he would
break into a grin!
[RYO]
As you see the ingredients
are essentially the same
as an acqua pazza.
But wrapping it in
heat‐resistant film
gives this dish a
different name altogether...
Cartoccio!
The dish I've served to you all,
is cartoccio of fall saury!
[SOMA]
Oh...
In the semifinals, he used
an "incendiary device",
which brought on umami.
And now he's introducing
a huge bomb of flavor.
Impressive.
Alright, stuff your fat face!
Mmmm... too delicious!
Fat of the saury so sweet.
Seems to melt...
dance in my mouth, yes!
[GIN]
The seafood is at the
peak of freshness...
it has incredible umami!
For him to infuse it like this
and give it such boldness...
it's almost too much!
This is the essence
of Ryo Kurokiba!
But there's even more
to it than that...
he developed such rich flavors,
using only a little seasoning...
Oh, there's something
refreshing...
Something different.
This is...
...Yes, herbal aromatics!
Exactly right!
When wrapping it in film...
I also added this...
An herb butter bomb
of intensity!
[ERINA]
He took regular
room‐temperature butter...
and added it to a variety of
thinly diced herbs and spices.
He then placed it in
the fridge overnight to rest.
And let me tell you it took its
glorious time melting in the
oven while basking in the heat.
Slowly penetrating
its rich flavor...
permeating the saury as well as
all the other ingredients!
[SENZAEMON]
That's what gave it such
flavor and aroma, like a
super dreadnought of impact!
It's a ferocious flavor that
runs through and through!
It looks like it's
going to happen.
Mother is going to...
Expose herself!
Whaaat?!
Right out in the open?
Seriously?!
I don't know if this
is appropriate you guys!
Ahhh!
[GIRLS]
Huh?
(Speaking clearly)
It was a splendid dish.
Truly, when brought
to the table,
it was like a visual
assault to the senses.
Even the way it was served
paid adherence to
the important elements
of the dish
as well as current
culinary trends.
Throughout this venue, people
leaned forward to gaze intently,
by which one can say the intent
of this dish was realized.
(Leonora in background)
As you are probably
well aware of this...
[ALICE]
You know when Mother
eats something delicious
she stops talking like
an idiot and starts
speaking fluently.
Oh yes,
almost forgot.
None of this makes
any sense. It's weird.
[LEONORA]
The mellowness of the butter
ties together the ingredients'
contrasting extracts,
while the herbs impart a
powerful flavor impact,
while at the same time
allowing the aftertaste
to not be too persistent...
[SENZAEMON]
This expanse of corrupt
deliciousness would not
have been possible
with any other fish
than seasonal saury.
It's the culmination of his
handling of his incredible
cooking techniques!
[SENZAEMON]
In body...
[LEONORA]
...and in spirit!
[GIN]
You become one...
[ALL]
...with the ocean!
[BOY]
Ryo Kurokiba is so awesome!
[STUDENT]
Even the school director
stripped it all off!
[RYO]
Let it sink in! Feel it.
Burn the power of my dish
into your head, Akira!
(Grunts)
[SATOSHI]
Judges. Akira Hayama
will be serving next.
[SOMA] Oh...
[RYU] Eh...
Dammit quit screwin'
around with me!
You think you can possibly
beat me with THAT?
Are you taking this
competition seriously?
You're not even close!
[AKIRA]
YOU wouldn't understand.
This goes beyond you...
Aroma can change one's
preconceptions of a dish.
[ERINA]
It can't be...!
A carpaccio?
[BOY]
H‐he's serving an appetizer?!
[GIRL]
This is a joke, right?
[BOY]
These are the finals!
[STUDENT]
How could he win
with an appetizer?
[ERINA]
Appetizers are a staple
of multi‐course meals,
intended to whet the appetite.
By nature, they're a
light menu item.
For him to choose that
as his dish is crazy.
[RYO]
Akira! I know that your eye for
ingredients is as good as mine.
You may have even
thought you've succeeded...
But by showcasing the fresh
sweetness that comes from
raw, top‐quality saury,
there's no way it could
compete with the impact
of my cartoccio.
It overwhelms the eater
with umami and aroma!
Well, let us begin‐
[AKIRA]
A moment please.
There is one last finishing
touch I would like to add.
He's going to use
a blowtorch to give
the surface some char?
So be it...
But there's no way it can
match the aroma depths
of young Ryo's
incendiary dish.
(Gasps)
(Moans)
Ohh!
[AKIRA]
Finished.
May I present to you...
my charred saury carpaccio.
(Crowd cheers)
[AOKI] Badass!
[SATO] Delish!
I'd eat the crap outta that!
It looks incredibly juicy
and decadent with flavor!
That's more powerful
than smokin' it.
[IKUMI] Oh!
[RYOKO] Amazing!
It's totally different
from anything!
[YUKI]
Whaaaatttttt?!
[ERINA]
It's so seductive,
it's enticing the eater
to shed its constricted dress.
Help! I cannot wait
a moment longer!
(Leonora foodgasming)
[LEONORA]
The dressing uses extra virgin
olive oil and wine vinegar.
Even the saury's liver
has been dressed.
The bold taste of the liver
spreads across the tongue,
accentuating the
sweetness of the flesh!
I feel I could drown in the
outpouring depths of flavor!
God! It's a compilation of
so many different spices
I can't think!
That's wrong!
He has used but only the
one spice known as allspice!
What the?!
He used just
one flavoring in that?
But isn't blending
a bunch of spices together
to create the ultimate aroma
his main weapon?
[ERINA]
No.
His ability to
manipulate aromas
is more than just
mixing them together.
By cutting back on flavorings,
he was able to elevate
the fresh taste of seasonal
saury to new heights.
Well then what was
that wealth of aroma
that came bursting out?
It was an even match
for Ryo's cartoccio.
Please, yes. That was not to
be possible just by charring.
Ha. It was kaeshi.
I brushed some on
the surface of the fish
just before serving it.
"Kaeshi, huh"?
You mean like tsubamegaeshi?
Kojiro Sasaki?
Obviously, you have no idea
what that term means.
And no, that's not right.
Okay listen...
Kaeshi is a seasoning made
by adding mirin or sake
to soy sauce.
It becomes a dipping sauce
for soba noodles,
when adding dashi stock
It's viewed as an all‐purpose
condiment for any number
of Japanese dishes.
And that is why, even with
the high temperatures of
a hand held blow‐torch;
it's hard to get a fish
to burn properly...
but the sugars in the kaeshi
make it easier to get
a good char.
I think I understand now.
By using a short burst of heat,
you were able to preserve
the saury's fresh flavor.
[AKIRA]
That heat caused both the
saury's fat and the sugars
in the kaeshi to bubble,
allowing it to
surface correctly.
In other words, I took the
conflicting theories of aroma...
and presented them both
on this single saury plate,
creating a balance.
[GIN]
Ryo Kurokiba
and Akira Hayama...
[SENZAEMON]
...have both evolved
as a result of having
clashed just once?
Ryo Kurokiba brandished
his mighty sword,
showing that even
through competition,
he had further honed
his explosive power
to incite hunger and raw power
to ignite the warrior.
[GIN]
The duck dish that Akira Hayama
served in the semifinals
was a flamboyant
presentation of spices,
wielding a bejeweled sword,
rich in design and decoration.
[SENZAEMON]
Yet how has Akira
come to us this evening?
Through precise selection
and exclusion...
he was like a keenly honed
rapier ready to
pierce the throat!
Grrr!
Uh?
Ahh!
Ha!
Uhhh...
[AKIRA]
A "one‐trick pony who's only
good at spices," was it?
You're learning what it means
to follow the doctrine
of knowing spices.
You're defeat is imminent.
[RYO] Urgh...
[GIN]
This is the true face of Akira,
the virtuoso of aroma.
The sheer might of
the saury was perfect...
a pin‐point shot of flavor!
A bull's‐eye!
Splendidly done!
Akira Hayama!
(Crowd cheers)
[BOY]
The head honcho
bared his chest again!
[MEGUMI]
Ah! The Moon's
starting to disappear.
Come on Soma
you gotta hurry up!
C'mon Soma!
You're running outta time!
(Silence but Soma's footsteps)
[SOMA]
Sorry for the wait.
Here is your final dish.
Oh my God!
It's almost too much to take.
To someone for whom rice
is a staple, this will
bring unbridled joy.
The sight and scent of it
are overwhelming!
Nukasanma, saury pickled
in rice bran.
(Crowd gasps)
[BOY] Did he say bran?
[GIRL] He pickled it?!
[BOY]
So he hadn't given up after all!
(Yuki sceams)
[MEGUMI] So delicious!
Man, when I first saw
his crusty‐lookin' fish,
I wasn't sure
how this would turn out.
Oh yeah. He pickled
that puppy in rice bran!
That's why it
looked so grody.
[LEONORA]
Oh! I can take it no more, no...
the scent of fresh rice!
[SOMA]
Now don't you worry.
I'll spoon it out soon enough...
please bear with me.
What! I swear, Young Soma.
That is not good.
Hurry for me, please!
[OIZUMI]
The others made quite the show
of making us look forward
to their creations.
And Soma is no different.
He has learned the art of...
anticipation!
There it is!
Finally, I say.
And now... tasting!
This I look forward.
(Glup)
Oh... hot...
Hu..hu..hu...
Oohhh!
The happiness of fall is
rushing through my body...
tip toeing through the leaves.
Such a soft and
fluid wash of flavor!
The saury was
charcoal grilled and then‐
[LEONORA]
Once it was charcoal grilled,
it was cooked with the rice.
Such attention to detail
is what resulted in
the rice's splendid depth of
flavor and refinement.
And the saury itself
is wonderful!
It has a depth of salt‐based
umami as well as a gentle aroma,
both of which spread across
the tongue in a dance of joy!
The quality of this rivals or
surpasses that of other two.
Tell me sweet boy.
Is this rich flavor the result
of pickling the saury?
[GIN]
Indeed. In Hokkaido,
it is a traditional
and long‐beloved favorite.
It brings out the umami...
reducing unwanted odors
from the saury,
increasing nutritional value,
and for some is
the best way to eat it.
Soma Yukihira, you've done
a brilliant job of lifting
the saury's true flavors...
It was a bit of
a race against time,
but nothing I couldn't handle.
I got the best saury
I could from the market
and did a lot of experimenting
with the possibilities
while they were fermenting.
And I tinkered with some other
aging methods other than
pickling, as well.
Now, when it comes to the very
best the season has to offer,
I couldn't come up with anything
that could truly compete.
But, at the last moment, I was
finally able to come up with
an aging method I was
happy with ‐ rice bran.
It was all thanks to Ms. Fumio
and her pickled late‐night
snack at the dorm.
Plus, I got a little help
from some of my friends.
They were my inspiration.
You're saying you
arrived at this method
of aging on your own?!
I thought your blade
to be blunt...
but instead, you presented
a fine sword indeed!
Like a sword‐smith forging
steel of historic renown.
You have struck your hammer,
on your own "sword of fall"!
(Crowd cheers)
He did really great
out there!
Yup! No complaints here!
That's sure to get him
great reviews‐
Ah! The director!
He hasn't bared his chest!
[BOY] Dude!
[STUDENT] Yeah.
[ZENJI]
And both Dojima
and Leonora...
have put down both
their chopsticks.
[SATO] That mean somethin'?
[OIZUMI]
Huh? Must be because Young Soma
lost too much time making up
for a less‐trained eye.
The idea for his dish must not
approach that of the other two!
[GIRL] Sure enough, there was
no way he could beat them.
[BOY] Yeah, I guess...
[STUDENT]
Like I thought, this battle
is going to be between...
[BOY]
...Ryo and Akira.
[SOMA]
I think you guys
might want a little more.
Anyone up for seconds?
This competition... is over
Oh, Soma!
This will now conclude...
all the judging for today‐
[SOMA]
Because if you were
up for seconds...
I was thinking I might pour in
a little splash of this.
[SENZAEMON]
Hmm?
[LEONORA] Huh?
[GIN] What?
(Akira &amp; Ryo gasp)
[SOMA]
My saury dish...
isn't quite done yet.
You are now about to witness...
...all of its sharp flavor!
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "A New Jewel"