(Digging in cooler)
What are you...
are you going somewhere?
Oh, sorry.
Did I wake you?
It's not even
light out yet.
I'm headin' off to
the fish market.
The fish market?
Are you going to
check out the saury?
I love the fish market!
Say, do you mind if I
tag along and go with you?
Sure, fine with me!
I'll go get ready!
I'll be waitin' outside.
[SOMA]
I need to come up
with some ideas...
there has to be somethin'.
Some kinda key to beating
Ryo and Akira...
and I plan on finding it!
[MAN]
Move it, move it!
[BUYER]
How much for one kilo?
[GUY]
Get me that one! The big one!
[MEGUMI]
Oh! It's really
bustling in here!
It kinda gets the blood
racing, doesn't it?
[SOMA]
Whoa! That amberjack is cheap!
And so is that
mackerel over there.
[MEGUMI]
Stop it Soma...
You can worry about the
other fish next time, okay.
[SOMA]
Oh! Yeah, I guess you're right.
[MEGUMI]
Have you been here before,
or is this your first time?
Oh yeah, my dad used to
bring me around here a lot.
Oh.
Here we go, Pacific saury!
Yeah, I think I'll be able to
come up with some trial
dishes pretty easily.
Back at home, Saury was one of
our fall staples at "Yukihira."
I'm good.
When it comes to saury,
I feel pretty confident.
(Gasps)
Huh?
Well, well, well...
It's Ryo!
Alice is with him!
Hey did you guys come to
check out the saury as well?
That's a coincidence.
[RYO]
Not a "coincidence"...
I come down every day,
so I can see what's fresh.
Really...
I come here only when
it's deemed necessary.
The market gets started
way too early for my taste!
[MEGUMI]
Eeeeekkkk! I can't believe
he ran into one of his
opponents here!
There's no way I can
lose this theme.
I gotta pick out some good saury
to get a leg up on these guys.
So I've been told,
a saury's body is kind of
puffy and swollen...
and their eyes will be bright
and clear when they're
at their peak freshness.
And they say when the tip of
the mouth is yellow...
that means it's not only
nice and fresh but fatty
and yummy too.
That's true, but you can't just
go about blindly picking one
because it looks like
it's "fresh".
It may not have fully
developed its umami yet.
You need to let it sit.
Sitting allows it to
develop inosinic acid,
an umami component.
The amount and speed
with which it develops
will change depending on how
it was brought in from the sea.
It takes a measure of experience
to gauge the right balance...
It's between
freshness and umami.
That's true, but being a
good judge isn't just about
using only your eyes guys.
You can use your hands too!
Gotcha!
OOh, amazing!
You're holding it by the tail
but it's completely straight!
That shows you that
the body is firm!
Judging by the bright eyes and
the belly, this one is fresh.
I have no doubt about it...
this looks to be the freshest
saury in this shop today. Oh!
You're wrong again.
I'll take...
THIS one right over here.
[MEGUMI]
Huh? That one?
Why would he bother
with that one?
It's smaller than Soma's
and the stomach isn't
as extended either.
[RYO]
Your face says you don't
agree with my choice.
Care to give it a try?
If we turn these guys
into some sashimi...
it will be clear which one
is the better saury...
Not to mention...
who's got better
judgment picking fish.
(Alice giggles)
I'm really sorry,
we shouldn't do this here.
No, no, no.
If you're students at Tohtsuki,
I don't mind at all.
(Crowd gasps)
[SOMA]
It's done!
[RYO]
Done!
Come try a bite,
Megumi Tadokoro.
[MEGUMI]
Uh...
There's really not much
texture here Soma.
I'm sorry but I had to say it!
[SOMA]
Hm...
Whereas the one Ryo picked out,
it has a nice and firm
feel to it. Not sure why.
That's easy. It's all because
of the time difference,
between the saury's rigor index
and its muscle‐breaking
strength.
[MEGUMI &amp; SOMA]
Ohhhh?
The rigor index is an
indicator of a saury's firmness.
To preserve the freshness,
the fish's blood is drained,
and gradually lowers
beyond the 10 hour mark.
You see, it's the muscle
breaking strength that
determines firmness,
and that begins to drop
rapidly after just about
five hours or so.
I see, so even if
the flesh is rigid...
it can still deteriorate
and lose all its firmness
once the five hour mark
has passed.
Correct. That's the pitfall
when working with a saury.
Whatever, that has nothing to
do with how I pick a fish.
Oh come on, Ryo!
And after I took
the time to explain!
[RYO]
You'll just know it...
Just pick somethin'
and touch it.
You'll know how fast
or slow it swam...
you'll know how it was
originally preserved...
you'll know if there was
enough ice when it was
finally transported...
You'll know everything there is.
Listen here, Soma...
The timing of the seasons
is absolutely crucial
for the quality and
taste of an ingredient.
In other words... choosing
anything less than the best
makes all the difference.
I'll let you in on
a little secret of mine.
There's a reason why I
frequent the fish market.
It's because if just a little
time goes by without doing so,
my senses become dulled.
I've done this for 10 years.
It's how I've survived and
how I will always survive.
I'm not gonna let some
half‐ass punk win this.
There's no way you'll ever
be able to beat me.
(Scared gasp)
Be seeing you guys around!
[MAN]
You know, there was
another young kid
from Tohtsuki Academy
here earlier.
[MEGUMI] Hmm?
Yeah, it was that tanned,
good‐looking boy with
the white hair, right?
(Both gasp)
[WOMAN]
He looked like he was
just walking around
with his head down,
but suddenly he just stopped.
[WOMAN] Oh!
Excuse me ma'am.
I'll take what's in the
middle of that box...
as well as the one that's
second to the left.
[WOMAN]
Can you believe he was able to
chose the best fish of the day
without even looking at it?!
[MAN] Oh really?
[WOMAN]
I mean it was like he could just
sense where the best fish was.
[SOMA]
Relying on my hands to judge
the fish isn't going to be
enough anymore, huh?
This is gonna change
everything for me.
Not choosing the absolute best
can ruin the entire dish.
It's ready.
Yep!
(Sniff) Ahhh!
Mm... Mm...
Mmmm...
My god that's really good!
That's the power of
fish being in season.
But I'm pretty sure those two
will find the very best
saury out there.
They'll find one better than
this one and they'll do it
on the day of finals too.
If you really want to get
better at picking out fish,
I guess you'll just have to
come here every single day
and try to figure it all out.
You're right.
But still, it's gonna
be pretty tough.
[YOUNG SOMA]
Look Dad!
[JOICHIRO]
Hmm?
C'mon, Soma.
That sardine's no good.
Huh? What's wrong with it?
There are countless things
you need to look for
depending on the type.
Even if you just concentrate
on one type of fish...
it will easily take you
more than 10 years to get
a good eye for it.
(Shock)
This could be pretty bad.
There are only 10 days
left until the finals.
Either way, no matter how good
I get at choosing one...
it will all be pointless
if I don't have a
solid idea for my dish.
That's the most
important thing.
That's certainly true.
[SOMA]
This is going to be tricky.
Both of those guys will
come out with dishes
that make the most
out of their saury.
I don't know
what I should do?
Even though I made it here,
those two are...
I dunno Megumi.
I feel... stuck.
[REPORTER]
Professor Shiomi, would you
mind telling us what kind of
assistant Akira Hayama is?
[JUN]
U‐um! Well, um...
Akira is a v‐v‐very talented
young man indeed!
A‐as an assistant,
he's just wonderful!
Um, his nose is a real asset to
our work here in the lab.
[AKIRA] Don't go getting nervous
over some simple interview, Jun.
[JUN]
I‐I just...
This is why you're
such a lab rat.
Please don't call me "Jun!"
So Akira, is it really true
that you're able to pick out
a good saury just by
the scent alone?
That's right.
As you know fish carries
a strong odor.
The smell is made of aldehyde
and other compounds and well...
these particular compounds
increase as highly unsaturated
fatty acids oxidize...
My nose can detect
the volatile components.
That smell is my tell‐tale sign.
There's also the scent of the
blood, that helps me determine
the degree of umami.
And Saury gives off a wealth of
information.
Allow me put it this way
for you to understand.
My nose can naturally detect
not just fresh saury,
but ones that are
perfectly suited to my dish.
[STUDENTS]
Whoa... Wow...
[BOY]
Hey Mitsuru, are you done
with getting the bio info
on Soma Yukihira yet?
Oh, ah, no...
No, I haven't.
I don't think he's gotten back
from the fish market...
and it looks like he hasn't
even started on his dish yet.
Sounds like he's
running behind schedule.
Like I thought, Soma's
not gonna make it in time.
Well people are already sayin'
that it's just gonna be
Ryo and Akira anyways.
[MITSURU]
Oh...
[REPORTER]
Ryo Kurokiba...
Akira Hayama is doing well
but it seems Soma Yukihira is
running behind on his schedule.
Would it be safe to say
that's one less rival?
I don't think of
either of them as rivals.
I couldn't care less
about Soma and Akira.
After all, I'LL be
the one who wins this.
I'm so sorry,
please forgive me.
but do you think you could
speak up a bit more?
Huh?
[BOY] Hmm?
[REPORTER]
What's this?
Is this what you're going to
use in your saury dish?
(Ryo roars)
C'mon! How long is this
interview gonna take?!
[RYO]
Get the hell out!
(Students scream)
Well in fairness,
he just barely said it was
okay to ask questions!
Judging by that curry battle...
I don't think his skills have
caught up to me just yet.
Sorry, Soma Yukihira.
[RYO]
You possess no FIRE
for this victory!
[AKIRA]
And Ryo Kurokiba.
I'll make sure to
burn you to ash, too.
I'll pay you back for
the insult of the semifinals!
I will shred you
all the way to the grave!
[AKIRA]
With a nose like this, losing to
you would be quite difficult.
[RYO]
Akira!
I will be the one to win this!
[MEGUMI]
I'm sorry, Ms. Fumio.
For having to come
all this way to get us.
[FUMIO]
I don't mind dear.
If we do well in
the Fall Selection,
it'll raise Kyokusei's
reputation as
a prestigious dorm.
Still, it seems like
our firecracker has
hit a wall, doesn't it?
It does.
I'm worried, he hasn't
moved from that position.
Poor boy... the odds are
stacked up against him
havin' to face those two guys
with such a good eye...
If the odds were
a little more even,
there'd be some way for him to
close the gap. I'm sure of it.
How so?
Like for example when to
sprinkle on the salt.
You know what I'm talkin' about?
Saury's flavor changes depending
on how long the salt sits
before you cook it.
Oh, I get it...
The flesh becomes more firm
as the moisture is removed.
The same as pickled vegetables.
That's right.
And you can expect
an increase in umami.
Trouble is, if you
let it sit too long,
you'll run the risk of
losing all its freshness.
[SOMA]
So it's about timing, huh?
When they're just
out of the water,
they haven't built up
their umami yet...
But if too much time goes by,
they lose their freshness.
But I've also heard
that these typically
have their best flavor
right before they're
about to go bad, though.
(Gasp)
Wait a second.
(Soma panting)
Hey Shun!
I've been looking for you!
I'm gonna need you
to come with me!
HEY, RYOKO!
(Banging on door)
[SOMA]
YOU IN THERE?!
Ehh...
[SOMA]
MEAT MEAT!!
(Soma panting)
Huh? Soma?!
Please come with me...
I need you.
Huh? You need me?
[SOMA]
Sorry for gathering you all here
on such short notice.
What seems to be
the problem, Soma?
Figures it would be
all about him again?
You'll have no chance of winning
in the finals without obtaining
the highest‐quality
saury, am I right?
The day of the finals...
I'm not goin' to the market.
(Gasps)
What do you mean you're
not going to the market?!
If everything goes
according to plan.
I'm buying my saury
a few days ahead.
I don't have much time
for trial and error,
but I'm betting I won't
need that time with
what I am presenting.
It'll be even better
than seasonal.
So then...
you mean that...
That's right,
I am going to age it.
To age it?
Oh! I like it.
Ryoko's rice malt...
and also Shun's smoking...
They're both knowledgeable in
how to age foods aren't they?!
[SOMA]
And you too, Meat Meat.
I know there's a lot
you can teach me
about protein.
I assume you wanna know
about aging beef.
It's a method of curing
where you expose it to air
while controlling
temperature and humidity.
An ingredient's flavor
isn't just about how
fresh it is, right?
If I can properly learn
to age it and bring out
all of its umami.
I'll be able to fight the
experience of those two guys.
So please...
I ask you...
Will you help me with this!
[MEGUMI]
Hm‐hmm...
Well, of course I will!
After all, you're one of us
you silly little goose!
Well, it's definitely
worth a shot!
Are you going to try
that out on Shun?
[SHUN]
Yes. I'm not opposed.
[SOMA]
All right!
It's time to try out a dish!
[OTHERS]
Yeah!
Hm... Those crazy youngsters.
[SOMA]
There are three ways
we can try aging...
salt yeast, smoking,
and THIS, which is
a high‐humidity fridge.
Hey. Thanks for
helping me out okay.
Uh, sure,
it's nothing really.
Just so we are on
the same level,
this method will take at least
three days to age properly.
Same goes for smoking.
It takes two days
to salt and dry it,
then one whole day for it
to properly mature.
The fridge is about the same,
three to four days as well.
Alright, so with
just this schedule,
we should be able to try
each method twice
as long as there
aren't any hiccups.
You're sayin'
we'll only have two tries?
I don't know whether that'll
be enough to beat their
trained eye...
THAT'S the challenge.
I can guarantee that
the rice malt will
totally permeate the saury.
But we must watch
the temperature.
You'll find subtle differences
in aging depending...
on liquid or smoking agents.
We need to be precise
with the setting.
Let's do 3 degrees Celsius
and 90% humidity.
That will allow the optimal
amount of moisture to
concentrate the umami.
Yes. Rice malt, smoking,
and now this...
they'll be done in three days.
I've gotta make use of
this wait time.
I'm going to do everything
I possibly can now!
(Music playing)
[RYOKO]
Are they finally ready?
[SOMA]
Yeah. There all done now!
Aren't they beauts?!
Well, let's give them
a taste then.
(Chomp)
That's really good!
They all have so much more umami
then I expected they would!
[IKUMI]
They turned out fantastic, Soma!
The one in rice‐malt has
a mellow depth of flavor,
while the smoked one gives off
an incredible smell.
[RYOKO]
And the humidity‐aged one
seems like it could be used
in any number of dishes.
Like foil cooked... marinated...
or even fried or grilled.
Or it could be totally
wonderful just as a sushi!
But it's...
[ALL]
Oh?
I still feel...
the saury that Ryo served
back at the fish market...
just tasted a lot better.
After all that, huh?
But these were aged
absolutely perfectly.
But you're still thinking
that it's not enough?
Hmm...
[IKUMI]
Hey, Megumi, will you tell
Soma something for me?
Tell him if he needs anything,
anything at all...
don't hesitate to ask.
'kay!
See ya.
I'll see you
a little later,
goodbye now.
[SOMA]
Well that didn't go as planned.
Maybe tryin' to beat their
saury by smokin' mine
is a dead end?
Maybe I should spend
at least a little time
trying to develop a better eye?
No, that's still
a little premature.
The aged saury definitely had
increased umami.
This has to be
the right approach.
I just don't have any
other direction to turn.
There's just one more chance
to experiment with the aging.
After that, I'll have to
do it in the finals.
So which one should I?
Should it be the rice malt...
the smoking...
or the humidity aging?
What can I use that
those guys can't beat?
I have to think.
I need something better...
Some kind of trigger for aging,
one that will develop
the saury's umami.
(Drip)
Hmh!
Guess I'll go buy
some more fish.
[FUMIO]
What going on with you, Soma?
[SOMA] Oh!
You seem kinda down.
[SOMA] Oh...
Your dishes won't turn out well
with you moping about.
Why not try and
pull it together?
You're gonna lecture me
while sittin' around
having a nightcap?
Hm...
Well, at times like these,
it's important to stop
and take stock for a minute.
[SOMA]
Hm?
(Gasp)
Huh?
I love you so much, Fumio!
[FUMIO]
Boy! You're gonna
spill my drink!
Looks like inspiration
has finally struck, Soma.
[SOMA]
Uh‐huh!
This just might work after all!
[RYO]
Soma isn't here again today.
[AKIRA]
What is he up to?
He hasn't come to
the market in days.
[RYO]
Has he thrown in the towel
already? I doubt it...
[AKIRA]
I don't see him as that type.
[AKIRA & RYO]
Just what is he planning!
[SOMA]
Hm...
[URARA]
Presenting the finalists
of the Fall Selection!
Entering the arena
are our three competitors!
The Aristocrat of Aroma,
Akira Hayama!
(Crowd cheers)
The Tyrant of the Kitchens,
Ryo Kurokiba!
(Crowd cheers)
And contestant No. 3,
from your neighborhood eatery,
Soma Yukihira!
(Crowd heckles)
Do it bro!
We're here for you, Soma!
You can do it Soma!
I believe in you!
[URARA]
And now the moment we've all
been waiting for...
the finals of the Fall Selection
are underway!
[SATOSHI]
Without further adieu, allow me
to present today's judges.
Oh! Look at Isshiki.
I know, it's hard to recognize
him wearing clothes, huh?
More importantly, did Soma ever
come up with a dish to present?!
Well we... we don't really
know that either.
Seriously?
[SATOSHI]
Up first, is our head judge:
school director,
Senzaemon Nakiri.
Next up, is our head of tourism,
Executive Chef of
Tohtsuki Resorts, Gin Dojima.
And we are honored
to have among us...
from Tohtsuki Academy's
research department
and head of Nakiri
International,
Leonora Nakiri!
[MEGUMI]
She's so pretty!
[YUUKI]
Look how pale she is!
[RYOKO]
Is she Northern European?
Oh, it's my Mother.
[YUUKI] Wha?!
[ALICE] Huh?
[SATOSHI]
Ms. Leonora oversees all aspects
of Nakiri International,
a world recognized
academic institution
known for the latest techniques
in fine cuisine and
molecular gastronomy.
A word, if you would
be so kind.
(Angelic choir singing)
(Clears throat)
H‐hello to everyone.
Um, yes, you may call my name
please, Leonora Nakiri.
I am living from
in Denmark, yes.
Judging will be tough
for me to try and eat...
But I try very hard, yes.
Her grammar's atrocious!
Gimme a break!
You could've at least practiced
before coming out here, y'know!
You need to get out of here,
this area is off limits to
non‐committee members!
[LEONORA]
Oh, Alice, are you well?
And Erina, are you well?
Is there something I say now?
I see Ms. Erina has quite
a temper, as always she does.
[ERINA]
It is all your
daughter's fault!
Hm... You are the
Soma Yukihira who beat Alice,
I hear you are, yes?
Quite surprised
I was to know.
So, your food is what
I am looking forward to
the most to eat.
Sound good, yes?
If it is not delicious,
I may be very upset
and angry on you.
[SATOSHI]
Contestants, if you would please
unveil your saury to the judges!
Oh! Such incredible luster
and with just the right amount
of firmness and fat...
It's like the glint
of cold steel!
(Swords clash)
Those blades are extraordinary,
perfectly suited for war.
Dammit!
Can Soma really pull this off?!
[MEGUMI]
Oh, Soma!
(Grunting)
[IKUMI] Ah!
[SATO] What in the heck is that?
That thing's got...
[GROUP]
...no edge!
[NARRATOR]
Next Time:
"The Sword that Announces Fall."