[SOMA]
What do you think?
Two kinds of omelet wraps.
Mmm...
This one has chili sauce, and
the other has a basil sauce.
Whatever, I could make these
way better than this.
What?!
All you two ever do is eat.
[SOMA]
So, Professor Shiomi...
This thing you mentioned...
the "Stagiaire".
What is it exactly?
Stagiaire is French for
"trainee."
So basically you're all going to
be helping out somewhere.
[JUN]
It's part of your
curriculum here.
All first years are sent
to train at different food
establishments.
Places can range from
high‐class restaurants
to food manufacturers...
Really all areas
of the public sector.
It's part of your studies,
a chance to learn what it's
really like on the job.
This will be
a piece of cake.
Even among all those pros,
I doubt there are many who can
do what I can in a kitchen.
It's not as simple
as that, Ryo!
[JUN]
Other things are at play...
Each location has
specifically asked
to take in Tohtsuki's students.
So if you think about
causing problems
and tainting the
Tohtsuki name...
know that some students have
been expelled on the spot!
Of course they were.
That's how this
school is operated.
So I'll be working
in a foreign kitchen...
That means I can get exposure
to the outside world!
So if we complete our work
without causing any problems,
then we should be
in the clear.
Again not so easy...
the basis for passing is to
leave a "visible accomplishment"
during your training period.
We need a visible
accomplishment?
(Crowd chatter)
[SOMA]
Let's see...
We're supposed to be
working in pairs.
I wonder who my partner is.
(Thud)
Mm?
Huh?
(Dumbfounded whimper)
It can't be you...
Soma?!
(Opening song)
[SOMA]
Well, let's do
our best, Miss Secretary!
Don't call me that,
you jerk!
I have no intention of
working with you at all.
So you just need
to back off of me!
I'll complete this
thing on my own!
Do as you please.
I wonder what kind
of place this is.
It's a bit exciting,
don't you think?
Don't ever speak to me!
[SOMA]
If Tohtsuki is bothering
to send us here,
it must be some super
luxurious restaurant!
[HISAKO]
Are you even
listening to me?!
[SOMA]
Really?
Well it's not quite
what I imagined.
[CUSTOMERS]
I don't have all day!
What am I supposed to do?
Eat in five minutes?!
Forget it!
I swear!
Aw, screw this!
I'm so sorry! Forgive me!
I'm so sorry!
Uh?
Could you be, uh,
the students from Tohtsuki?
[BOTH]
Hm?
(Laughs) Looks like you
caught me at a bad time.
Um, I'm the owner Mitamura...
Welcome aboard, guys.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Hisako Arato,
and I'm here for the week.
Pleasure to be your stagiaire.
I'm sure I have little to
offer your restaurant, but I'm
grateful for the opportunity.
I'm Soma Yukihira.
It's a pleasure.
Huhhh...
Hisako Arato and Soma Yukihira?
[MITAMURA]
Well, sorry to get right
to it, but, uh...
could I maybe please
get your autographs?
Huh?
I mean, come on!
You're students
of THE Tohtsuki Academy!
You could go on to
become superstar top‐chefs
known throughout
the entire world!
He kinda reminds
me of someone...
Hey, Soma!
[HISAKO]
He's mistaken...
I'm not the kind of chef
anyone would be proud of.
Not anymore.
[SOMA]
Hisako, you done?!
Don't talk to me
while I'm changing!
Do you have
any manners?! (Growls)
[SOMA]
Whatever...
Feels pretty weird
to be wearing anything
other than my
Yukihira apron.
Huh?
Sorry for the wait.
Y'know, that apron
really suits your style.
Gaaah!
[SOMA]
Hey, this is the first time
we've been able to
talk like this, huh?
I mean, you're always
hanging around with Erina.
Uh?
Oh, yeah!
Next time when you see her,
will do me a favor‐
That won't happen.
Huh?
There won't ever be a next
time for Erina and I.
Having failed her
in the Fall Selection,
I don't have that right.
Oh yeah, you lost
to Akira, didn't you?
Shut up, you little punk!
[HISAKO]
Miss Erina is the embodiment
of perfection in all she does.
She can't have a loser like me
to be at her side...
it would lessen Miss Erina's
reputation.
(Sigh)
Stop standing around.
Sure is quiet in here...
Makes you forget all
that commotion earlier.
All right! Let's do
our best today.
Hisako, for starters,
will you‐
Don't you dare
order me around!
Listen! You may have
experience in the kitchens,
but don't put on airs!
I've taken courses
on forming teams
and cooking in
an assembly.
Plus, I easily cleared
that 200 speed challenge
we had at the training camp.
The Stagiaire will be
no problem for me!
I understand
that, but...
those situations don't involve
multiple random orders
coming at you all at once.
Random?
(Rumbling)
Uh!
No!
[STAFF]
They're here!
(Crowd chatter)
[HISAKO] What is this?!
It filled up in seconds!
Yes, of course! Right away, sir!
What can I get for you, sir?
[HISAKO]
We're swamped out there!
One omelet A Set and one D Set!
I need lunch special for three!
How did it get like THIS?!
[MITAMURA]
Back in the day...
It used to be that our only
regular customers were locals.
Then the rail line went in.
Now we get all the customers
trying to catch their train.
And, well, they like to show up
right before having to board...
They all order
at the same time...
AND they all try
to pay at the same time.
This is way too much
to have deal with...
Um, is our food
ready yet?
My food had better
get here soon!
Hey, is that A Set
and D Set done yet?!
Hold on,
five more minutes!
The dishes are
piling up!
I need some help
over here!
[FEMALE STAFF]
Where are all
the dishes?!
Ah! I can get the dishes!
(Loud stomping)
[CUSTOMER]
That cut it pretty close! We'll
need to run or we won't make it!
Thank you. Thank you.
Please come see us again!
(Deep sigh)
(Loud stomping)
Huh?!
Uh!
They're here!
[STAFF]
Next train!
Just when I thought we were
done, the next group moves in!
It's like a battlefield!
They just keep coming,
with no time to breathe!
'Kay, I got another
order up!
Table 1:
One special sandwich,
two French toasts,
three hot coffees.
All coffees for
after the meal.
Table 3: Two beef stews,
two spaghetti napolitans,
one hot coffee, two iced
coffees, one melon soda.
Hold the bell pepper on one
of those napolitans.
(Chatter)
Our food is taking
forever today.
At this rate, we're
not gonna make it...
Hisako, hold down
the front house.
Uh?!
[SOMA]
Table 4: napolitan
and other items are up!
(Amazed gasps)
[CUSTOMER]
Excuse me!
I ordered a cheddar cheeseburger
and this is not it!
I'm very sorry, sir!
I'll fix it right away!
Forget it, I don't have time!
Hisako, communication's failing
between front and back.
Can you take a look?
(Growl)
How dare you order me!
Who do you think
you're talking too?!
I'm not one of
your lackey's!
Grrrr!
Guh!
Everything about you is
limited, I'm afraid to say.
[SOMA, FLASHBACK]
I understand that, but...
those situations don't involve
multiple random orders
coming at you all at once.
I have no right.
I can't go back and show
my face to Miss Erina.
(Whimpering)
Dammit!
[MITAMURA]
Thank you guys so very much!
[STAFF] (Sighs)
I can't believe we made it!
We finally finished!
You were amazing!
We truly could not have
done this without you two!
(Sigh)
I'd say he's
a keeper!
Tohtsuki students are on a
completely different level.
(Praise continues)
Yeah.
He also has some
great experience
working in the kitchens.
Don't short change yourself,
we meant you too.
(Gasp)
Oh yeah!
Come dinnertime,
you had the whole
system down pat.
You're a fast learner,
and you're really smart too.
You were a big
help out there.
What?
Thank you... very much.
Hng!
Don't ever touch me like that!
Good job today!
I can't wait to
see how we'll do
here tomorrow, Hisako.
Uh.
Guh!
[HISAKO]
Stop talking to me like that!
[SOMA]
Yeah, yeah, I understand.
Yeah I don't think so.
What did you just say to me?
Eeeeeee!
I'm telling you I refuse
to wash any of your dishes.
Assigning lowly base chores
to one such as I...
is a foolish command decision
on your part and nothing more.
Don't push your luck,
little girl!
You're nothing special
from where I'm standing.
[MEGUMI]
Oh, Soma, I have a feeling
things are going to get rocky!
[MALE STAFF]
Man, those students
were a big help again.
We really hit the jackpot
with bringing them on.
Is that a picture
of this restaurant?
It is. This was taken
way back when my father
was the head chef.
I can still remember it...
All the folks from
the area used to
really love it here.
You have a great
restaurant here.
You have a wealth
of dishes to offer.
And you're
so considerate.
(Chuckle)
That's one thing
I'm still pretty proud of.
I try my best to maintain how
the restaurant used to be.
(Chuckle)
Hmm...
Where do you get off
slacking on the job, Soma?
You're not even
done cleaning yet.
I wonder if
this will do...
Huh?
So, uh, "a visible
accomplishment."
Is this what
they meant by that?
What are you
talking about?
Our training is going
exactly as it should.
Yeah. I suppose it is,
but still...
Hey, I wonder how the others
are doing at their stagaire.
Where do you think
they ended up?
(Deflated sigh)
Miss Erina is sure to
be doing splendidly...
even without me there
to help.
[CUSTOMER]
It was simply divine today.
So wonderfully refined,
much more so than before.
The courses both excelled
in freshness and boldness.
It was perfect!
At this rate, you're
sure to get a Michelin
star next year!
Ah,yes... Thank you
very much, sir.
(Seething grunts)
(Smug laugh)
[COOK 1]
Miss Erina,
a taste test please!
[COOK 2]
Miss Erina,
here's the mise en place!
You need to
pick up the speed.
You're running about
50 seconds behind.
Forgive me!
It'll do.
You may take this
out to the customer.
Ma'am!
My beautiful castle...
That little girl
has ruined it...
She's taken control of it
in the blink of an eye!
Excuse me, Chef.
Huh?!
When it comes to poaching
the main dish...
(Growling)
Listen to me on this.
You need to lower the
temperature a bit more,
so that the current levels
will further accentuate
the ingredient.
And there are
at least 12 other points
I'd like to discuss with you.
Would you care to hear my
opinions now or later?
(Intense growling)
(Fuming grunts)
If you would
be so kind.
[ERINA]
The first is regarding
the hors d'oeuvres.
What should I do?
Is there something
I can improve as well?
[SOMA]
Yeah... there's
still something
not quite right.
Why are you still
going on about that?
What is it
that's not working?
[HISAKO]
The flavors are good,
and everyone on staff
is kind and really enjoys
working at the restaurant.
I'd like to help them
as much as I can
but I don't know
what you're talking about.
[SOMA]
Are you really okay
with this, Hisako?
Ah?
I get the feeling
that things
aren't really going
very well, are they?
(Gasp)
I think that
the shop
needs to make
some changes.
Also...
Nah, never mind.
See you. Until tomorrow!
(Wind whistles)
[MITAMURA]
Oh, good morning, Hisako!
Could you go over the
expense sheets today?
Yep. I've already
made some headway.
Oh. Great.
Carry on.
This restaurant needs
to make some changes?
Just what is that
supposed to mean?
I don't get it.
I get the feeling that things
aren't really going
very well, are they?
Hmph!
What does he
know anyway?
See there?
Ever since we've
been working here,
the sales are going up
and complaints are‐
(Gasp)
This isn't good...
So once we leave here...
[SOMA]
Yup.
(Gasp)
Things will go right
back to how they were
before we arrived.
Uh?!
Maybe they could
keep things running,
if they got a few temp
workers to help them out
around the busiest times.
But I doubt it would be
a permanent fix for them.
Hm...
Maybe things are fine as they
are...
Ahhhhhh!
We're holding an
emergency meeting!
At this rate, the Stagiaire
will end with me just
doing the dishes.
But I don't know what to do.
I'm not amazing like
Erina Nakiri.
There has to be something.
I have to help somehow!
If you would, please.
Ah! Okay!
Hah?
[MALE STAFF]
We should go looking for
some more part‐timers.
We need to get some
workers lined up down here
before these two have to
leave us and go back.
Agreed. But do you think
we'll be able to find people
who can fill
that void so easily?
[MALE STAFF 2]
Oh...
May I? Maybe pare
down the menu.
(Gasps)
Having so many dishes can
end up being a hindrance.
If you print a new menu,
leaving just the popular items‐
I can't do it! Some of
those recipes have been here
since back in my
grandfather's day!
But at this rate, this
restaurant is one day bound to‐
[FEMALE STAFF]
Now listen...
You two have been
a really big help
since you've been
here, but c'mon...
You can't just change
things... not this.
Some of us have been working
here all the way back to the
previous owner.
If we changed the menu,
it wouldn't be Mitamura
anymore.
(Sigh)
Isn't that doing a
disservice to the customer?
They specifically chose to
come to this restaurant.
Whether the food is delicious
or not doesn't matter if you
can't even serve it, right?
(Grumbles)
[SOMA]
Mitamura...
Huh?
What kind of place do
you want this to be?
Uh...
[SOMA]
Please... There's something
I'd like you to hear...
[MEGUMI]
Excuse me! Um...
What do you want?!
I discovered something
that I think might help
improve the fish salad you're
serving for the second course.
Now YOU'VE got something?!
Just go back to
washin' dishes!
Ah! Okay!
I'm sorry! Aaaah!
It's fine. You may
go ahead and speak.
(Grumbling)
It's just, uh, I was thinking
it would be better
if the customers had the
chance to choose the amount
of sauce they wanted.
Looking at all the dishes
that come back...
I'm seeing a lot
of leftover sauce.
But on the other hand,
when customers sop it
up using the bread...
there ends up being a few
more leftover vegetables.
Well isn't she something?
She was able to
improve things just
by washing dishes.
Still, it might be
too hard to fix.
I'm sure it would cause more
traffic in the kitchen
and in front‐of‐house.
No it wouldn't.
We could always just place
the sauce in a saucer
and serve it that way.
It's a widely popular
serving technique
throughout France.
Though it's known as a
traditional method...
it could be seen as
something fresh and
new with customers.
Enough of this nonsense!
Don't forget, customers
are here for MY food!
Who cares how much
sauce they get?
[WAITER]
Um, Chef!
What now?
One of our customers
is asking for more sauce
for her fish course.
(Stammering)
(Gleeful laugh)
Please come again!
Thank you for
choosing Mitamura!
[MITAMURA]
You want it to be
reservation only?!
You already know
your food is delicious.
There's no doubt about that.
You have a refined touch,
and the extensive menu leaves
customers satisfied.
But things change.
Your situation is different
than it was before.
And it's putting a dent
in how good this place is.
So I thought this might be an
option that could work for you.
[SOMA]
Though I do feel bad for the
people off the street.
So you think
reservation only?
It's easy enough
to implement...
but do you think it'll
go over well?
There would be a pretty
big risk of us
potentially losing
all of our new customers.
[FEMALE STAFF]
We've always done things
the same way around here...
I don't know about suddenly
changing everything.
[HISAKO]
Your situation has
changed though.
You need change as well,
or the avenues open to you
will be closed.
If there really is a way for
you to achieve something...
then you need to set your pride
aside and latch onto it.
I think this restaurant
has outstanding potential.
But you have to...
You have to believe
in yourself.
[SOMA]
Well, in any case,
it's not up to us.
That's for the guy at the top.
That would be you.
[SOMA]
As a chef, what is it
you want to achieve?
Ah, welcome!
Mr. Shimizu. Thank you
for your reservation.
Sure. I'm just sorry
it's been so long.
Your place just seemed
so busy all the time
I didn't want to intrude
for just a single.
Once I heard you were
reservation only,
I called right away!
I'll take my usual order:
Spaghetti Napolitan...
Oh, and if you would‐
Take it easy
on the salt, yes?
That's right! There's a
third‐generation owner for ya!
(Chuckles)
[SOMA]
Here's your order, sir.
(Sniffing)
Mm...
Mm. Just what
I expect.
It's delicious as
it always is.
Could I get a coffee
once I'm done, please?
Yes, of course, sir.
It seems they've cleared one
of the components already.
The Stagiaire is going well.
[NISHIZONO]
They recognized simply
performing the task
with no clear aim
is missing the point.
They then explored what
they could do for the shop,
and acted upon it.
That is where the first step
of the Stagiaire begins.
You looked a bit dismal
the first day...
but you've perked up
a bit since.
Heh! Where do you find all
this extra time to blab?
You should be working,
Soma Yukihira!
You are welcome!
You meant to say,
"Thank you very much."
"Please come again,
Glad you enjoyed"!
Hm?
Don't go being original!
You two have passed
Stagiaire No.1.
What?
I have no complaints
with your work.
Thank you so
very much, ma'am.
How was she watching
us this whole time?
Tohtsuki is
pretty awesome.
You should be receiving papers
for your next training
assignment tomorrow morning.
I hope you perform well.
(Chuckle)
Hey, by the way,
you plan on goin' back
to Erina soon, right?
Agghhh!
Um, what's with you?
You need to
lighten up already.
[SOMA]
At least hear me out.
I'm all nervous!
Why'd this have to happen?
That is an unusual
amount of luggage.
Go ahead and get in
if you can fit.
(Nervous sigh)
There's something
I don't quite get.
How has someone of
your caliber gone
unnoticed till now?
I‐I can't take all
this attention!
(Nervous sigh)
So how were your grades
whenever you advanced
to the high school division?
Um, the truth is,
they were pretty
below average...
I can't tell her they were the
absolute worst in the school!
[MEGUMI]
But you know, it wasn't just
me that turned things around.
I needed help making it
through training camp.
And competing in
the Fall Selection...
well that was thanks
to my dorm mates.
They were a huge help.
And then of course Soma
was always there for me.
Uh!
The first time I saw
Soma I stayed away.
I thought he was
nothing but trouble
and should be avoided
at all costs...
But before I knew it,
we'd become friends.
Do not ever mention
his name around me
ever again!
(Grunting)
Ah! I'm so sorry!
Why does talking about
Soma upset her so much?
By the way, where is Hisako?
I'm used to her
always being with you.
(Sigh)
Wh‐what did I say?
Are you all right?
Hisako...
[YOUNG ERINA]
Come on, Hisako.
The cherry blossoms
are so pretty!
(Laughing)
Aw, come over here
and spin around with me!
I couldn't possibly
do that.
I must always stand
behind you, Miss Erina.
For I am here as your attendant.
Hmm...
[ERINA]
Hisako, back then,
all I really wanted
you to do... was...
[HISAKO]
Pitiful, isn't it?
I still don't have
enough confidence.
I think up till now, I've always
been perfectly at ease...
Content to walk behind
Miss Erina forever.
I never thought I was worthy of
being able to do anything else.
(Yawn) So, what're
you worried about now?
Were you even listening to me?!
I was, and the
answer is easy.
From now on, don't just
stand behind Erina...
You should think more
of yourself and stand and
walk at her side instead.
(Gasp)
Don't forget,
I lost to Akira too.
But one day,
I'm gonna knock the
wind outta his sails!
You got that?
It's just that...
I feel that having
lost just once,
I don't have
that right again.
"If there really
is a way for you to
achieve something,
then set your
pride aside and
latch onto it."
You know you
said that yourself?
Oh, I almost forgot.
These belong to
someone in my dorm.
They said it's okay
to borrow them.
(Gasp)
[SOMA]
I promised Erina
she could read them,
but never had a
chance to go over there.
But this'll
be perfect.
Now I don't have
to go... Sweet.
I'm counting on you, girl.
Don't go quitting on me, okay?
Soma, I'm...
I'm very honored.
Thank you for this!
Come on over here, Hisako!
(Laughing)
(Light chuckle)
I'm in the
same boat.
But in the end...
(Ending song)
I wasn't just following my
father's footsteps...
I was finding out my own
reason to cook.
I'm gonna devote myself...
to the world of cooking that's
outside of "Yukihira"!
That way, I'll shed new light
on discovering my own,
unique flavors!
All right!
Where's the next Stagiaire?!
[Narrator] Next time:
"The Magician Returns"