Scallops! Scallops! Okay?
It's all about scallops!
Lobster! Lobster!
It's all about lobster!
You got that?!
You wouldn't know!
You want a piece of me?!
I don't think so!
You don't understand how
it's better than scallops!
Scallops, you hear me?!
Scallops!
You need to take
your country ass back
I'll crush you
in the face!
You need to take
your country ass back
I'll crush you
in the face!
to wherever it came from!
Go back? You'll have to find out
before me what's the best...
Lobster is the king of the sea!
Go back? You'll have to find out
before me what's the best...
Lobster will crush you
and your stupid SCALLOPS!
it's SCALLOPS!
Lobster will crush you
and your stupid SCALLOPS!
The director
has his brush!
Who's it gonna be?
Who's the winner?!
(Urara):
And the winner is...
Ryo Kurokiba!
(crowd cheering)
Megumi's just didn't
make it happen...
It didn't make...
the director bare his chest.
(Urara):
Thank you, everyone
for attending.
This concludes today's food
battles for the Fall Selection.
See you all tomorrow...
when the third and fourth
battles will be held.
Please take care
as you file your way out.
We should go
and see Megumi?
Let's do it...
What the?
Where's Yuki?
MEGUMI! Huh?
Did you see that?
He was terrifying!
(sobbing)
I know! I totally get it.
You were like a
sweet little rabbit
(sobbing)
frightened by a big, nasty feral
dog wanting his bone to eat!
(applause)
frightened by a big, nasty feral
dog wanting his bone to eat!
Huh?
(applause)
Megumi! You were
terrific out there.
Miyoko Hojo?
(Male Student 1):
You killed it out there!
(Male Student 2):
Can't believe you went
toe‐to‐toe with Ryo!
(Female Student):
That was an awesome battle!
(Male Student 3):
Guess it wasn't just luck that
got you through the prelims!
Uh... thank you...?
Thank you all. Your judgment
was much appreciated
and your cars have
been prepared for you.
A driver will
be waiting.
Right this way.
Grandfather?
Are you alright?
It's nothing, child.
I just need to use
the washroom.
Megumi Tadokoro,
was that her name?
That girl must possess
immeasurable latent potential.
That's the only explanation for
this unraveling of my region.
She disrobed me without me
even realizing it.
(Senzaemon):
The 92nd term...
This is an
age of kings!
(Jun):
There you are!
Hm?
What are you doing
out here by yourself?
Ah, nothing much, really.
I just wanted to get some
night air before tomorrow.
Look Akira...
I don't want you to worry too
much about having to win, okay?
Just making it through the
preliminaries has made me
really, really proud
of you! I'm so happy!
You're going to be
up there on the big stage,
so just enjoy
yourself... 'kay?
If I don't take
this seriously,
then I'll never
achieve what I want.
I am making it to the top.
That, I will.
(Isami):
Brother... have
you packed everything
you're gonna need tomorrow?
Oh... and please be sure
to take that good luck charm
I gave you.
I've got it.
Also, this is a "sleep easy
pillow" I bought for you.
And I'll light an aromatic
candle for you tonight.
You should probably
calm down, Isami.
Sorry... I'm praying you'll
give it everything you've got.
(Isami):
I know you can win.
Don't worry about me,
little brother.
I've been improving myself.
I wanna get through the finals
and face Soma Yukihira again.
(Takumi):
Just you watch...
There's no way our
Italian cuisine can lose!
I will do you proud,
Ms. Erina...
By these hands...
I WILL win tomorrow!
That's my girl.
I'm looking forward to this.
For Jun's sake....
For Isami's sake...
For Ms. Erina's sake...
I cannot lose!
(Urara):
And so... the curtain
rises on day two
of the Fall
Selection finals!
We'll be holding the third
and fourth battles today...
featuring four contestants
who made it through
the preliminaries.
What kind of heated battle
can we expect to unfold today?!
Soma sure is
running late.
Jeez. He needs to get
his butt here and watch
so he's ready for
his next bout!
Well, I couldn't
get him to wake up.
Maybe I should've
been more forceful
and just dragged
him over here...
Well, he has been pulling
all‐nighters lately.
But it looks like he's
finally left the dorm room.
He'll be fine.
(yawning)
Yo. We meet again...
Soma Yukihira.
I remember you
from the preliminaries.
(Yua):
93 points!
Soma ties for 2nd place!
And that's your final tally!
Sorry 'bout that,
transfer student.
I didn't see ya there.
C'mon, try not
to look so pouty...
(Subaru):
Soma Yukihira.
What do you say we head
to the auditorium together
and check out
what's goin' on?
Uh. Yeah, sure,
why the heck not?
All right. Hang on a sec.
(Soma):
That ride looks
pretty hardcore...
This guy seems like
some crazy biker type.
Sorry for
the wait, dude.
That was a heck
of a long wait.
Was it necessary
for you to cover it
AND have to rope it off?
Takin' precautions like this
is only a natural reaction.
I'm registered against
theft, of course...
and have a GPS service
installed on it.
So if my ride ever gets
stolen, I'll know exactly
where it was taken.
Are you trying to
threaten me somehow?
I have a credo that I
always like to stand by
both in the kitchen
and out of it...
"The devil is always
in the details."
Good to know...
This guy's actually
kinda particular.
(Soma):
You wouldn't think
it by the looks of him.
I ain't introduced myself
yet, huh? The name is...
(Subaru):
Subaru Mimasaka.
Remember that.
He's the eighth contestant
in the finals.
(Soma):
That's one
awesome name, bro!
(Subaru):
Right?! By the way, this
is hand embroidered.
You serious...?!
Yeah...I embroidered
it myself!
That's awesome!
(Urara):
And now... the third battle
is ready to begin!
Today's theme is that
American favorite
that has evolved
far beyond fast food...
and is now a worldwide staple!
The hamburger!
The American standard is a
cooked patty between two buns...
but contestants
are free to choose
which ingredients
and type of bun.
Okay... it's time
for our finalists to enter!
It's gonna start now!
Where is that boy?!
Oh... I'll go look
for him outside.
(Akira):
Hey... pass this on
to Erina Nakiri for me.
I'll be taking that next seat
on The Council of Ten.
I'll also be taking the top spot
here at the Tohtsuki Academy.
Please keep such foolishness
here and here alone.
Ms. Erina's successor
to The Ten will be ME.
So back off.
(crowd cheering)
(Urara):
Here comes the man who
manipulates spices at will,
the one who took
the top spot at A Block...
Akira Hayama!
He's up against the contestant
who got the Number 2 spot
in B block with her
medicinal curry...
Hisako Arato!
It's a match between a spice
and a medicinal expert.
(Male Student 2):
They're different fields...
but they have
similar approaches.
It's like a battle of the herbs.
NOW LET... THE COOKING BEGIN!
Is that...?
(Ikumi):
it's a kebab! Akira
made a DAMN doner kebab!
Is that Turkish, or what?
Yes. Doner means "rotate,"
and then kebab means "to roast."
(Zenji):
Heat is slowly applied
as the meat turns...
the flavor of the fat
blends with the spices
as it continues to roast.
OH, YEAH! The smell of
that fat is ON, my brotha!
Yeah! I'm
freakin' out, here!
(Sato):
What's up with
that secretary chick?
(Aoki):
Dude... DUDE! Are
you seein' this?
(Sato):
It's like, movin' around!
Huh?! That's...
(Yuki):
It's softshell tortoise!
Wait, she's
makin' what?!
...a gnarly tortoise
burger, brah!
Breaking down a
softshell tortoise
uses a technique
called YOTTSU‐OROSHI.
(Zenji):
You turn the
tortoise on its back
and watch for when it
extends its neck...
She didn't flinch at all.
(cheering)
(Ryoko):
She pouring something into
the blood she just drained...
Is she using saké?
Isn't it supposed to keep
the blood from congealing?
I bet she's going to
smash it into a patty!
(Sato):
(wretches) OhmyGod!
That's so nasty!
(Aoki):
Those tortoise guts
are grossin' me out!
(Nao):
Even covered in fresh blood...
her expression
is so dignified...
You're beauty knows
no bounds... Mistress!
(Saotome):
Daylily and WU WEI ZEI
are medicinal herbs.
Ginger and Shaoxing wine?
Mm‐hmm.
(Bald Judge):
By simmering those
with the shell,
it seems she's trying to make
a rich and flavorful broth.
Soma, you need
to hurry up!
Come on, Akira and Arato have
already started their battle!
Yeah, I'm comin'
So... who is... this "Arato"?
Hisako. Erina
Nakiri's helper!
Oh. "Miss Secretary"?
Jeez... you've only
met her like, 10 times.
You should
know her name!
(laughs)
(Soma):
Oh yeah, I ran into
this weird dude.
Soma Yukihira. You
have a small restaurant.
You've used your
experiences there
to create wildly
imaginative food.
You take great pride
in its namesake.
At the training camp,
you made and an OKAKI‐AGE
and a soufflé omelet.
Height is 171 centimeters.
Weight 57 kilograms.
Blood type: B,
shoe size: 26.5 centimeters.
Average sleep time
has been six hours, 14 minutes.
You were in Class 5 your
first year, Class 2 your second,
and Class 7 your third.
The devil is always
in the details.
Takumi Aldini...
Son and heir to a
TRATTORIA in Tuscany.
Born to a Japanese father
and an Italian mother.
Height: 168 centimeters.
Weight: 54 kilograms.
Blood type: A.
Holds a fierce sense
of rivalry toward Soma.
Lives with his brother Isami.
Calls home twice a month.
Has a fan club at Tohtsuki's.
Doesn't like heights.
Interested in
Japanese food replicas.
Sets two alarms
when going to bed.
Has a mole on his left shoulder.
Prefers showers over baths.
Is bad at poker.
Most of his underwear
is checkered.
And the thing most
important to him is...
(Megumi):
Um... I think! This is the area
where we're standing now!
I'm sorry, Soma!
This is my fault.
I don't know
where we are.
No worries.
What's this? You lost
or somethin'?
If you want you're welcome
to watch it on the monitor
in my waiting room.
It's just right
over there.
Soma?
(Takumi):
Megumi?
I swear...
How did I
end up ib=n here?
What's the
friggin' harm?
(Subaru):
You already finished goin' over
your ingredients, didn'tcha?
Take whatever snacks ya fancy.
(Megumi):
Oh... thank you very much!
Whaddya think about
this match... any thoughts?
Yeah... I don't
really know...
I've never seen Miss Secretary
cook in a battle before.
What do you think
about it, Megumi?
Um... I know...
Hisako's specialty
is medicinal cooking.
But I'm not sure medicinal would
be a good match with hamburgers.
In any case it looks like
the first one to finish...
is gonna be Hisako Arata.
(Ikumi):
She mixed diced tortoise
meat with ground pork
and is now kneading
it all together.
And it looks like she's
seasoned the mixture
with salt and pepper
to make her patties.
Then she wrapped it some
glorious pork caul fat.
(Yuki):
That fatty membrane
lets her cook it
without it falling apart.
(Young Erina):
Hisako!
Hisako, come on!
The cherry blossoms
are so beautiful!
(giggles)
(Hisako):
The girl called
the "God Tongue."
What I wish more
than anything
is to always serve
by her side...
to walk with her... if even
just a few steps behind.
For the sake of that wish...
I WILL make it through
the Fall Selection and beyond!
I shall unveil a dish
that will rattle the senses!
I present to
you gentlemen...
a soft‐shell
tortoise burger!
(Urara):
Okay folks...will the
judges take it soft on her
or give her a SHELL of a time?!
(Saotome):
This Chinese steamed
bread has both resilience
and a distinctive
subtle sweetness!
(Oizume):
(hearty bite)
All the hairs on my body
are standing on END!
My whole body...
It's like
it's on fire!
(soft‐shelled laughs)
Whoa!
They're so shiny and sparkling
with the bloom of youth!
That's the power of the
soft‐shelled tortoise.
The thick meat of this patty
melts in the soft
pallet of my mouth.
It overflows with the
umami of the fatty tortoise!
The sauce ingeniously
incorporates the turtle stock!
It blends with the patty
to create unparalleled
depth of flavor!
The tortoise blood that I added
to the patty was used in a way
to warm the meat
from the inside. Also...
I grounded the shell
and managed to work
the powder into the patty.
Dried tortoise shell is used
in Chinese herbal medicine.
It's seen as a potent tonic
for a variety of ailments.
(Sato):
It's in both the
sauce and the patty!
(Aoki):
Now I get why the judges
looked so insanely stoked!
(crowd chattering)
Enough!
Only one with experience
could grasp the quintessence
of this highly involved dish.
(Senzaemon):
The answer lies in
the gelatinous nature,
the viscosity
of the tortoise.
That is exactly right, Master.
(Hisako):
Such viscosity greatly
affects the flavor profile.
Not to mention...
THIS patty also contains
a wealth of not just stock
but dissolved gelatin, as well.
There is one area
of the human body
that is most sensitive
to physical stimuli...
it's the roof of the mouth...
the soft palate.
The meatiness of the patty and
the creaminess of the sauce...
provide an almost
seductive experience.
Put simply...
this is a jolt to
the senses.
Not just to the
sense of taste
but to the sense
of touch, as well!
(Senzaemon):
It's like the sheer
sensuality of the tortoise
leaves you nowhere to hide!
(heroic battle cry)
(flat roar)
This deliciousness...
it's positively monstrous!
I was intoxicated
without realizing it.
(Megumi):
I‐it's... incredible!
She was able to actually
use medicinal cooking
even in a
hamburger battle!
Yeah. If you go up against
her at any time...
she would bring that level
of knowledge to the table.
But still...
this battle belongs
to Akira Hayama.
Huh?
(shocked oohs and aahs)
What's this? The second Akira
began cooking his patties...
the faces of everyone changed!
(crowd cheering)
(Akira):
It's not always what's
inside the mouth.
Not in the world of taste.
It's ready.
(Urara):
The aroma of Akira
Hayama's hamburger
is spreading
through the venue.
Folks are
getting excited!
We can't wait
to meet this meat!
(Sato):
Smells rad, man!
(Aoki):
It's like a thick Hamburg steak
topped with roasted kebab!
Hurry up! I
can't take it!
The judges are totally
begging like starving dogs!
Apologies for the wait.
What are you up to,
Akira Hayama?
Something like that would surely
make the taste overpowering.
No matter how you try
to entice them with aroma,
what you really need
is a refined FLAVOR.
I was in such
a daze I didn't...
realize we already
ate it all!
(Senzaemon):
So he went with pita bread
for the "buns", did he?
Pita bread...
This Middle Eastern bread
is cooked at high temperatures
till it fluffs up, creating
a pocket that's filled
with a variety of
different ingredients.
Where to begin...?
(Senzaemon):
The smell of the kebab is masked
by a homemade yogurt sauce,
elevating the aroma
of the spices.
What's more is his
genius choice of a patty.
It's used as a kofta...
a Turkish meatloaf
that pairs ground beef and lamb
with a variety of spices
and minced onions.
It's an assault
on the nostrils!
What's going on?
His patty was
so thick, but...!
Allow me explain.
Four ingredients are needed for
a hamburger. You will need...
(Akira):
the buns...
the patty...
a sauce...
and pickles.
The sharp flavor and
acidity of the pickles
helps to make the umami
of the meat stand out.
They are the secret
star of the dish.
It looks like you
used shredded ginger
to try and fill that role...
but if you ask me...
that was na ve.
Really? Well, then
what did you use?
Do you really wannna know
what I used for my pickles?
I used achaar.
(gasps)
What makes achaar?
Well it's an extremely
acidic preserve
that's made out of
vegetables and fruit
pickled in
mustard oil.
I used onions to make
this particular achaar.
The nose‐tickling scent
of the mustard oil
elevates the umami of the meat,
bringing in the flavor.
(Akira):
For acidity, the star
player is amachur,
a powdered condiment
made from dried mangoes.
I used lemon juice to
accentuate the acidity,
then further enhanced the
overall experience
by adding garlic, chili peppers,
cloves, cumin seeds,
black pepper, paprika powder,
and to give it sweetness...
honey and a
touch of ginger.
(Senzaemon):
The scent of pickles
made by one with an
exceptional sense of smell
is an honor one never forgets.
It takes both
the meat's fattiness
and the smell of the lamb
and combines them into
a desirable experience!
This was an explosion of taste
and the senses
of the creative mind!
When it comes to curry and
spices, his talent is limitless.
(Saotome):
Akira Hayama...
His potential could rival
even the God Tongue!
We have decided the winner
of this hamburger battle!
I am aiming for
the top spot.
Anyone who tries so hard at
staying in the number 2 spot...
is hardly a worthy
opponent to face.
What was that?!
Everything about you is
limited, I'm afraid to say.
Including your ambition...
as well as your culinary view.
I don't want to
concede to him.
But the moment I caught
the scent of his food
and allowed it
to touch me...
I felt an incessant hunger
that stripped me bare!
In this third battle,
the winner is Akira Hayama!
(roaring applause)
I lost...
Hisako.
I'm so very
sorry, Ms. Erina.
(sobbing)
Excuse me. The fourth battle
is about to begin guys.
Anyone not competing, please
relocate to the audience.
Ah! Sorry about
that Eizan!
(Megumi):
We'll go now!
(Takumi):
Soma.
After this Selection
is played out...
I WILL settle that battle from
the first day of training camp!
Oh, you mean the one that Hinako
totally avoided judging?
(laughs)
That takes me back!
What?! In any case, I'm going to
defeat you once and for all!
One day, Soma...
I will challenge
you to a Food War.
(Takumi):
When that happens,
I will utterly destroy you.
(Soma):
This guy's the same age as me,
but he's come so far.
Always being at the
restaurant, I had no idea.
Sure thing... Takumi.
So you better
not lose today!
After that we
can figure it out.
And see who'll
destroy who!
Ah... Yes...
yes of course!
(Takumi):
Agreed!
You know, that
guy Mimasaka...
By all accounts, Hisako
made an incredible dish,
but he was still so
certain that Akira would win.
He has a certain unique talent.
To Subaru Mimasaka,
Tohtsuki Academy
(Eizan):
is the perfect playing
ground for someone like him.
(Takumi):
Hey.
I'll thank you to keep
your hands off my things.
I've seen you around.
I know you've been stalking me
these past few days.
What do you think
you're getting away with?
You're okay with this?
Such
crappy old utensils?
You would only be able
to make trash food
with these cheap
little things.
Are you trying to provoke
me? I see through you.
(Subaru):
There's something I've
been wantin' to ask you...
(Subaru):
It's about your brother.
Since he was a kid,
he's been lacking in the
cooking department, hasn't he?
It's obvious he's a second‐rate
chef with no potential.
It takes all he's
got just to keep up
with your
looming shadow.
How does it feel to have
such a dimwit of a brother
dragging you down?!
Bastard!
Yeah... you're right,
you filthy Italian mongrel.
This is gonna be a
one‐on‐one bout, so...
(Subaru):
we gotta enjoy it
to the fullest!
TAKUMI ALDINI!
(cackles)
(Yua):
Are you in there Urara?!
This is really bad!
What is the
matter with you, Yua?
This just came in!
(horrified gasps)
(Urara):
Attention... I have an
announcement for everyone
in the audience.
The next food battle between
the opponents Subaru Mimasaka
and Takumi Aldini...
will be held as a Food War!
A Food War?
(Narrator):
Next Time:
"The Pursuer."