[ISSHIKI]
What's wrong, Eizan?
You're looking somewhat down.
[EIZAN]
What are you
talking about?
The venue is whipped up
into a frenzy.
This year's Selection
was a complete success.
Nothing could make us
administrators any happier.
Still, this seems like
a rather different scenario
than what you'd originally
hoped would play out today.
Hehe. I don't know what
you're talking about, Isshiki.
It was you, wasn't it?
Who pitted Mimasaka
against Soma? Well played.
[ISSHIKI]
With Takumi being taken
out as he was...
You knew Soma was sure
to accept Mimasaka's challenge.
To him, there would be no
greater shame than losing in
front of everyone,
and failing to avenge
his friend.
You played this in
the shadows...
so as not to dirty
your hands.
That's so like
you, Eizan.
But your plans...
well they didn't work out
exactly the way you thought?
You may have come up
with a scheme to get
him into your clutches,
but it was Soma who
made short work of you.
He drew you in, didn't he?
What was that?!
I think you guys might want
to have a little more.
[SOMA]
Anyone up for seconds?
This competition... is over.
This will now conclude all
the judging for today‐
[SOMA]
Because if you were
up for seconds...
I was thinking I might pour in
a little splash of this.
HMM?!
(All gasp)
[ISSHIKI]
Or, to be more precise,
you may not have been
the only one, y'know.
Don't worry, it's probably
the same for everybody
here at Tohtsuki Academy.
Hm...
It's just that
my saury dish...
isn't quite done
being presented yet.
[ERINA]
Is that...
a white soup?!
(Opening Song)
[SENZAEMON]
I would be honored
to have seconds.
(Chuckle)
[ALICE]
Soma Yukihira...
You're always free to try one
last and futile tactic,
but come on now...
Don't you think you're just
trying to rehash my idea
from when the two of us fought
earlier? That's pretty sad!
[ERINA]
No, you're wrong,
Alice.
This is something else.
I present to you
my completed saury dish...
Seasoned saury rice,
soup style!
Alright, order up!
The soup has a slight
thickness to it.
It's blending with
the rice beautifully,
forming a subtle bond
of acquiescence.
(Slurping)
(Gulp)
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Aw yeah! There it is!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
He bared his chest!
This dish is now
so mellow and creamy.
It seems this white soup
is made of...
soymilk!
That's correct.
I used soymilk
with a bit of miso
and parmesan cheese added in,
and then I let it slowly
simmer over a low heat
until it was ready to serve.
It's made from Soymilk?
(Gasp)
It looks like you've
finally got it.
Usually the key to soup
is the dashi fish stock.
But for this soup
he replaced the dashi stock
and used soymilk
for the soup base.
I see what you mean...
Dashi fish stock is
essentially umami itself.
And like dashi,
soymilk contains plenty
of glutamic acid.
So it could easily
be substituted
and serve as the base for
all the flavors of the soup.
[ERINA]
Plus, umami has a
synergistic effect.
When two elements
are present,
the dish becomes
even more delicious.
With the inosinic acid
of the saury
and the glutamic
acid of the soymilk
it makes sense
to combine the two.
He created a
soymilk rice soup...
This is quite
interesting indeed!
(Slurping and gulping)
And plus, adding the
soup causes some of
the other ingredients
to suddenly make
their presences known.
And what's this that's been
mixed in? They look like...
Crunchy pickled plums!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
Crunchy pickled plums?
What the huh?!
He's bringin' out
the snackiess again!
The plums go on to become
an important element.
They lend a pleasant
crunchy texture and are
pleasing to the eye.
Their brisk flavor helps cut
the fattiness of the saury,
giving the dish a fresh,
bracing acidity.
He's made full use of
acidity's ability to
increase one's appetite.
What's more, is that
these Japanese plums
are made by being
pickled with salt.
They are the perfect
adornment for the aged saury.
However, what's especially
noteworthy is the parmesan
cheese that's added to the soup.
The addition of this
Western ingredient
mixed in with the Japanese
ingredients like pickled saury,
pickled plum, and miso
has created an all‐new
deliciousness!
It takes me back...
to when I met that man...
that man I hold
most dear to my heart.
(Laughing)
This way!
(Gasp)
Though from different
countries and raised in
different cultures...
when our hands
finally clasped...
it was an encounter
like no other.
(Giggling)
(Crowd gasps)
You're joking, right?
Those are some great
reviews he's getting!
Don't tell me that transfer
student is gonna...
[ISSHIKI]
Have you read this yet, Eizan?
(Gasp)
The latest TohSpo.
According to the
Journalism Club,
stories that bashed Soma
ended up selling more
copies than any others.
Well, of course they do.
After all, he referred
to this school
as merely a "stepping
stone" for him.
You can tell from the
audience's reactions:
that he's
"the transfer student,"
hated in both
name and deed.
I'm not so sure
about that.
In the end, I can't help but
think there's more to it.
He fought neck‐and‐neck
with Akira Hayama
in a spice battle.
In the semi's,
he beat Alice Nakiri,
blood relative
to the Demon of Cooking.
And then he brought
down Mimasaka,
a beast with
99 Food War victories!
But that said, many students
still don't want to acknowledge
Soma's abilities.
Why do you think that is?
I asked Soma's father what
he thought of all this.
It was enlightening.
[YOUNG SOMA]
Hey, Pops!
Watch out!
'Cause I'm gonna become
a chef and beat you!
That's quite
ambitious of you.
Well, good luck
with all that.
Great! Let's do it!
It's a food battle!
[JOICHIRO]
The way I see it,
it's not like Soma had any
special talent for cooking.
That's just something
a kid would say.
I thought that once
he'd lost a few times,
he would eventually
just drop it.
But...
Soma has never gotten
discouraged
in all this time.
And slowly,
one step at a time,
he's reaching his goal.
I didn't see it at first...
Until one day I noticed there
was something about Soma.
That he's missing something
that others hold on too.
And what is that?
Everyone wants
to believe that...
if you lose to someone
talented, it just can't
be helped. Ya know?
That's how people keep
a lid on their hearts,
because they want to preserve
their pride, or sense of
self‐worth, or whatever it is.
But Soma doesn't have that
"lid."
He's the first one
that will go headfirst into
anything he's not good at.
That's an unbelievable
strength, one that I could
never possess myself.
Soma's food has a
certain "spark" to it.
But rather than it being
the result of some sort
of genius‐like ability...
it's simply hard work.
A countless, obsessive stream
of trial and error.
It's something anyone
can do, but the fact is,
they don't bother to.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
He's got no chance
against him.
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
He's up against Akira Hayama,
the Master of Aroma.
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
And Ryo Kurokiba is an elite
chosen by the Nakiri household.
[SCHOOLBOY 4]
How could he win? I can't
think of any possible way.
[SCHOOLGIRL 1]
It's hopeless for him.
[SCHOOLBOY 5]
I mean, come on,
it's the genius who will win.
[ISSHIKI]
Why do you think that is?
Why look down on Soma
for excelling?
Because they can't
acknowledge him.
If they did, they'd be admitting
that they themselves don't try.
(Grunt)
Hmph.
Just wait... I feel the tide
will be changing very soon.
[SCHOOLBOY 1] It's pretty
awesome, huh?
[SCHOOLBOY 2] Big time.
He's battling them
on equal terms!
Both of those monster chefs!
You think he could
really pull it off?
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Yeah, there's no way
you can't acknowledge
his mad skills!
[CROWD]
Soma...
[SCHOOLBOY]
Soma Yukihira is...
[CROWD]
...awesome!
You're welcome!
[SENZAEMON]
This concludes the
final judgment!
We have made a decision!
(Crowd cheering)
[YUKI] (Excited squeal)
How d'you think
this is gonna turn out?!
He'll be fine, I'm sure.
He can do it!
He totally can!
Come on, Soma...
Soma Yukihira...
He made up the
difference for his fish
AND put out
a dish like that!
Peculiar.
You really are quite
peculiar, aren't you?
[SOMA]
(Big inhale)
Alright, for better
or worse...
the moment of truth...
[ALL THREE]
...is here!
I'll begin by saying,
masterfully done.
This was a clash between
individuals worthy of
being in the finals...
and all of you
successfully showed us
your approaches to taste.
Let's being with
the cooking skills...
In this respect, all three
were evenly matched.
[SENZAEMON]
Next, we judge you on your
ability to choose ingredients...
this undoubtedly goes to
Ryo and Akira.
They've shown to have the skills
to pick the absolute best saury.
However, Soma was able to keep
up through use of that
ingenious technique.
His creativity and perfect
execution of it sets him
above the other two.
(Crowd gasps excitedly)
(Excited gasp)
Yes!
[SENZAEMON]
However, we were
surprised to learn
that in our final judging
all three dishes
were essentially matched in
terms of deliciousness.
(Crowd gasps)
With all that said
and ruminated over,
the deciding factor...
was whether or not
the dish showed
the essence of the chef.
Huh? The essence of
the chef? Wait, what?
[LEONORA]
Yes, Soma. The essence
of the chef.
You see if a dish truly bursts
with one's originality,
then by simply tasting it
the essence of the chef's
aura and personality
should become visible
in the mind of the eater.
To put it differently, a dish
only that chef could make...
one that displays their
true ingenuity.
And we like to call
those sorts of dishes...
with all due respect
toward the chef...
Their Specialty!
He who will take top honors....
will be the chef who
probed deepest within
to show us his dish...
who truly faced the question,
"What is my cooking," and how
can I represent that?
And the name of
that person is...
(Slow heavy heartbeat)
(Raining)
[AKIRA]
I know nothing... not my
parents face's nor my own name.
All I know is that I was
abandoned on the outskirts
of the slums.
Left as a baby
to fend for myself.
This isn't the
right place for you.
Would you like
to come with me?
Your sense of smell
might be the evolution that
changes the food world!
[AKIRA]
I was rescued from
the slums I once knew.
Thanks to a woman
named Jun Shiomi
At the time, Jun was studying
under Professor Hayama,
the man who would become
my guarantor.
I was given a name: Akira.
It means, "A child who
would shed light, illuminating
a new culinary world."
And Jun was always at my side.
Never leaving me.
(Grinding)
[JUN]
Akira is a very
good boy, Professor.
He always gives his all
to help me with my research.
He's the perfect
complement for me.
I'm really grateful.
But I fear perhaps it's
too much for him.
I'm worried.
No, afraid.
I'm afraid for what I'm doing.
I fear Akira is doing
things he doesn't want
to do just to help me.
(Quiet crying)
[AKIRA]
No...
You're wrong about that, Jun.
You're the only one
who always saw value in me.
[JUN]
This isn't the
right place for you.
Would you like
to come with me?
[AKIRA]
You gave me a reason
to want to live.
You illuminated ME.
That's why I have to win,
for Jun's sake!
(Slam)
I must come up with something!
I have to win with a technique
no one else can copy,
or there's no point
in making it.
[AKIRA]
The power of aroma will
change the world of taste.
THAT is my style of cooking!
I'll give them everything...
everything I am
on a single plate!
The winner is...
Akira Hayama!
(Crowd cheering)
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Akira!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
[SENZAEMON]
The grilled saury carpaccio!
Akira Hayama's dish was
worthy of being called
a "specialty" item.
(Seething groans)
(Cheering continues)
Congratulations, Akira!
Ah!
I'm so proud! Congratul‐
(Intense sobbing)
You did it, Akira!
You really did it!
Thank goodness!
Oh, thank goodness!
Look at you. You're as
cool and calm as ever.
Get a little happy,
why don't you?
You know you‐
(Gasp)
(Crowd gasps)
Huh?!
(Screaming)
(Gasp)
A‐Akira!
Why would you do that?!
What's wrong?!
It's... nothing.
(Rustling)
Akira, did you know that
the aroma of cinnamon
has the effect of lifting
one's spirits in an instant?
Ah, yes.
[GIN]
The expression he had
at the semifinals...
I'M the one who'll
be moving forward.
I won't let anyone
get close!
[GIN]
It wasn't a smile
of confidence after all.
It was a means
to inspire himself.
Yet was threatening
in its display.
[GIN] That's scary good.
[LEONORA] Huh?
Akira Hayama, that was
some splendid cooking.
Thank you, I did my best,
Chef Dojima.
Take heed, when talent
is too great,
it can turn its talons
upon itself.
I hope that you're
able to keep that
talent of yours
in check for both
yourself and for Jun.
Huh?
Geh!
You freaking moron!
My God! You suck, suck,
suck, suck, suck!
I can't believe you'd
lose when I was right there
watching the whole time!
You're such a stinky
rotten boy! I can't even!
Will you stop hitting me?!
Get off me or I'm
going to end you!
I don't believe this!
How dare you use
that tone with me!
I am so done with you!
Come apologize when you've
learned your lesson.
AAGGHHH!
[YOUNG SOMA]
Watch out! 'Cause I'm gonna
become a chef and beat you!
Hm?
C'mon, Soma, that
sardine's no good.
Huh?!
But don't go losing to anyone
until you've lost to me again.
Akira...
Huh?
Are you still able to
make that carpaccio?
I think I should have
enough leftovers...
Let me try a little.
Huh? What? Why should I‐?
Let me try.
Uh, the thing is, it's‐
Hey! Let me have some of that
loser stuff too, you loser!
Why do you always have to be
so obnoxious?
(Both munching)
Okay. You satisfied?
No! But I bet I could make this
dish way better than this!
Ugh. You're such a sore loser.
Now listen: Tonight, we've
come up with a ranking system
for all the first‐years.
And naturally, I'm sitting up
amongst the top of them.
so you'd better watch how
you speak to me from now on.
You understand?
You wanna throw down right now?
Bring it on, quick silver!
Sure but the results
would be the same though.
[SOMA] Now, now...
[BOTH] Huh?
I must say, you made
a pretty decent dish
over here, buddy boy.
I just told you to speak
to me with respect,
you third‐place nimrod!
We don't know what
place anybody is!
Don't go getting
full of yourself!
(Garbled) Do you think you could
actually do better than me?!
[SOMA AND AKIRA]
Don't talk with your mouth full!
(All three bickering)
Well, I guess there may
be no reason to worry
about him, after all.
[GIN]
Those three look as though
they're going to make a
most interesting trio.
[LEONORA] (Laugh)
Why, yes they do.
It's by smashing against
each other that raw ore
becomes polished.
I believe that is Tohtsuki's
sole philosophy.
Indeed. Presented tonight
at the final selection,
another new "jewel"
has been rendered!
(Applause and cheers)
[EIZAN]
Tch...
You were great! I couldn't
be more proud of you!
[YUKI]
All right, suckers!
Tonight, we're gonna celebrate
Soma winning the semifinals!
Let's tear it up, right?!
[AOKI]
Yeah, in Zenji's room!
(Phone vibrating)
[ZENJI]
Why is it always in my room?!
[SATO]
'Cause it's nice
and big, bro?
Ugh! Sorry, you guys
go ahead.
(Phone ringing)
[SOMA]
What's goin' on, Pops?
Hey, Soma,
it's been a while.
[JOICHIRO]
So, how did finals go for you?
Uh, well, you see...
I sorta‐
WHAT?! You're sayin'
you lost?!
Who the heck won then?
Akira won.
Ah, Jun's apprentice, huh?
C'mon now. I don't wanna
lose to someone like Jun.
You feel me?
(Mocking laugh)
[SOMA]
He always gets so strangely
excited when cutting me down.
What kind of parent gets happy
when his own son loses?!
But seriously though...
his sense of smell is
really somethin' else.
It wasn't just his gift
of smell that did it.
There was something else
about it...
[SOMA]
It was like it
had purpose.
Hey, Dad, I'm glad
I left "Yukihira."
Hm?!
Otherwise, I...
I'd be missing
out on learning so much.
I think going forward, I'm out
to look for the answer to one
question...
"What is the dish that...
that only I can make?"
[SOMA]
Without that, I'm nothing.
You there?
Okay I take it
from your silence
that I must have said
something wrong. Sorry.
[JOICHIRO]
Nah, you're alright.
That's a good way to put it.
(Yawn)
[SOMA]
Alright, I guess I'm
boring him.
[JOICHIRO]
See ya, son.
(Phone clicks)
Ugh...
So you finally found it...
Amongst your peers you've
found the ones that will
drive you forward.
That's good. You're learning.
[JOICHIRO]
It's these relationships that
will drive you forward.
Embrace them while you can.
[JOICHIRO]
You can always turn towards the
plate for answers,
but if you're alone,
all that'll change
is your reflection.
My food.
How do I find food
that's uniquely mine?
(Ending song)
Hey, girls! Hello!
Meat‐Meat's here!
Welcome back!
[IKUMI]
Thanks for inviting me.
So, you got ahold of
some good wild game?
[YUKI]
Yeah, it looks
perfect to eat!
[MEGUMI]
There!
You look great in this.
It really suits you.
Oh, thanks a lot, Megumi.
Okay! Let's begin
the massacre!
(Girls cheer)
(Laughs)
How wonderful!
I love seeing such dainty young
women standing in the kitchen,
having a good time.
From where I'm standing, those
girls are anything but "dainty."
[IKUMI] You like that, do you?!
Rawr!
So, by the way,
where's Soma?
Oh! He went over to hang
out with some friends.
[SOMA]
And so you see...
that's why the
mildness of the soymilk
is able to highlight
the gentle saltiness
of the delicate saury
in a beautiful synergy.
Still, the crunchy plums
seem like a pretty cheap
addition to me.
I can't even finish this!
You're totally eating it
all up, idiot!
Gimme some more.
Must like something
about it!
Yeah, the cartoccio
I made for you yesterday
was way better than this gruel.
HUH?! Why don't you try
making it again?!
We'll do an
eat‐and‐compare!
That's all well and good,
but why are we doing
these taste tests here?
I've made some tea, guys!
[AKIRA]
What? You don't have
to do this, Jun.
Woah! You don't need to
serve these idiots our
best gourmet cookies.
Just give 'em some
of the old ones.
I heard that,
you tightwad.
A specialty dish...
[RYO] You're a friggin a‐hole.
A dish that shows
the essence of the chef...
(Bickering continues)
Something Akira
has that I don't...
Ahhhhhhh...
Hey, you're supposed
to savor those!
Akira.
I wanna do an
eat‐and‐compare.
Make that scorched saury
carpaccio again.
Make that two, m'kay.
Just shut up and go home!
[SOMA AND RYO]
Chop‐chop.
[AKIRA]
Don't you "chop‐chop" me!
(Chuckle)
[AOKI]
I don't understand it.
I can't believe he'd
climb into bed
with those dillweeds
he lost to!
Yeah. It's like the dude
ain't even upset!
Oh, Soma's upset
alright.
In fact he's so upset
he can't stand it.
Huh?
That's why he's
with them.
You see, the only way one
can learn who they truly are
is to step outside
their boundaries and
experience others.
And well... even if that means
turning toward the very people
who've bested them.
Obviously, the girls
certainly feel the same way.
[ISSHIKI]
No matter how small...
they're all learning
something from their opponents.
And Soma's no different.
Crap. Ain't no way we're
bein' left behind!
[AOKI]
Let's throw it down!
It's a Festival of Test Dishes!
[SATO]
We'll do it up, ninja style!
[BOTH] Time to get this party
started, mi bro‐migos!
(Zenji protesting)
[AOKI]
Shun, get your
skinny ass over here!
What's the matter, Shun?
Are you not going along?
Ah, could it be that
you prefer to mingle with
the fairer of the sexes?
Oh Shun, you dirty
little dog, you!
Well, not that there's
anything wrong with that.
[JUN]
In any case,
this is the only chance
you'll get to relax
and enjoy your time
as first‐years here.
(Slurping)
"Our only chance"?
What does that even mean?
Well it just means
that pretty soon
you boys will all be tossed
out of Totshuki Academy.
Huh?
You're about to begin...
The on‐the‐job
training program...
Known as a Stagiaire.
A Stagiaire?
(Narrator)
Next time: "The Stagiaire"