[AKIRA]
The first dish holds...
a little turmeric and pink
peppers and cumin...
and coriander and then cloves.
The dish to the right has
amchur, cardamom, dill,
bay leaves, and savory herbs.
And the dish over to the left
has star anise, fennel,
wild yam, and lemon balm.
[JUN]
That was terrific, Akira!
Even without being able to
see or touch them...
you guessed them all 100%!
That's right.
I'm completely ready for this.
[RYO]
106... 107...
108... 109... 110... 111...
112... 113...
I would say it looks like you're
completely ready for this.
114...
Jeez, you smell
like rotten death!
And you're sweating
everywhere!
Uh...
[ALICE]
I wanted to ask if you'd
like to go clean my room...
but you'll have to
take a shower first!
[RYO] Mistress.
[ALICE] Hm?
You're in good spirits
after losing to Soma...
So maybe consider...
That is WHY you lose.
Just a thought.
Ha! That's a cheap attempt
at provoking me...
but you're on Ryo!
And please, no wimpy tears
when you get destroyed.
(Crowd cheers)
I'm gonna crush you!
Yeah? I don't feel like
I'm going to lose
to some glorified attendant.
I give my own orders here.
[SOMA]
Hmmm... those two are up next.
I wonder what kind of bout
this will be...
Why are you acting like you
have the right to be here?!
Well, it looked like
the bout going to start,
so I didn't have much time
to waste.
I mean, which of
them is gonna win?
[ERINA] What are you doing
in here?! Get out of my face!
This is going to be one exciting
bout to keep an eye on,
Move it already! Who do you
think you're talking to?
don't you think?
You're barely even a chef!
What's he? Why's he over
there with Erina Nakiri?
Huh?
[MEGUMI]
What's he doing?
(Ikumi gasps then grunts)
[GIN]
We now enter the last
bout of the day.
As with the first round
in this semifinal,
the theme will be a dish
showcasing Western food.
Contestants...
LET THE COOKING BEGIN!
(Crowd cheers)
Dude! Look who's pulled out
his ingredients.
Is that a chicken?
It's not... That's...
...a duck!
[SONOKA]
Duck has a distinctive
flavor to it.
How you temper that is key to
the outcome of the dish.
That's the "scent expert,"
Akira Hayama, huh?
That fool sure knows how to
play up his strengths all right.
Lets see what he
offers up to us.
A chef's taste buds should
draw on his past experiences.
What he can make
depends on those factors.
Yes. If, along with
a refined palate,
one could also distinguish
between the scents
of mixed spices
they would double their
culinary expertise and
become unstoppable...
[GIN]
He has a sense of smell
like no other...
and he's studied at Tohtsuki
Academy since his first year
in middle school.
Akira Hayama is definitely
one of the elites.
One of the candidates
likely to succeed
Erina Nakiri on The Ten.
We know where
this is going.
Yeah. No question,
it's most definitely
gonna go to Akira, huh?
[SOMA]
You know, rumor has it that
Akira totally has the advantage
for today's semifinal bout.
What do you think, Erina?
Yes, well...
I have been in a few of the same
cooking classes as Ryo before.
Even if I was being
kind about it all,
I couldn't say the food he put
out was all that interesting.
I wouldn't really
rank it up there as
a total failure per se,
it just seemed
kinda perfunctory.
Like he was just doing enough to
fulfill the class requirements.
That's why I was so surprised
to see the originality of his
food in the preliminaries.
Oh, you are always
so clueless, Erina.
(Gasp)
[ALICE]
Hmph! If you'll excuse me.
(Grunt)
If you really wanna
know the truth.
Ryo's abilities can't be
measured through logic.
(Crowd gasps)
[BOY] Is he using eel?!
Is he for real?
I heard seafood was
his main specialty,
but this is an
unexpected turn.
Could it be...
a Kabayaki?
After all...
the theme is Western.
Eel is used in
several recipes,
not just French but
other high‐end cuisines
around the world.
It's not found just in
Japanese food anymore .
[ERINA]
Eel. Could he possibly
be going for it?
Say, what did you mean before
about the whole logic thing?
How is Ryo's food
measured exactly?
(Alice giggles)
For YOU to start talking
philosophical jargon...
is insane.
Your whole doctrine
when it comes to cooking
is based on science and logic.
There's nothing philosophical
about Ryo's cooking.
In a very real sense, there's
something about the taste
of Ryo's cooking that transcends
the usual measure of logic.
[YOUNG RYO]
I have to win...
If I don't, I'll have
nowhere I can say I belong!
Here, today,
either I win or die!
[ALICE]
Ryo has made it through kitchens
that were more like the pits
of hell than an actual kitchens.
In such terrible environments...
the only thing he could
rely on was his skill.
In order to survive, Ryo
cultivated absolute attention
toward perfecting the most
difficult of flavors...
And he did so with an
all‐consuming fighting spirit
that burns from within!
Everyday it's always there...
Ryo and I constantly wage
culinary wars with each other.
And yet not a single
day has gone by
that he hasn't given it
everything he's got.
Once he gets a taste of
victory, it's over.
It makes me think...
If there's one thing I'm lacking
when it comes to competition...
I'd say it would be...
(Erina gasps)
[SOMA] Hm?
[ALICE]
Hmh? Oh, nevermind.
If there's something
I lack about competing...
it would be tenacity.
A tenacity that burns
throughout my entire body.
Becuase here, among all
these amazing chefs,
the one for whom
that tenacity burns the
absolute hottest is Ryo.
That knife is specially
designed to break down eel.
Masterfully done.
Has he mastered the techniques
of Japanese cooking, as well?
[GIN]
This competition card is
like a steller's sea eagle,
flying ever‐higher...
and a fierce tiger that
crouches in the earth,
devouring all
who dare approach!
(Eagle screechs)
(Tiger roars)
[RYO]
I'm not really feelin' it.
You possess no FIRE
for this victory.
[AKIRA]
Hmph...
This is a battlefield down here!
Anyone who isn't prepared to win
should get out while they can!
Quite possibly.
And you may be right
about one thing.
I do have less of
an imperative to win.
But you're forgetting
something...
with a nose like this...
losing to you would be
quite difficult.
Y'think so huh?!
(Sizzling)
Now...
Play me a sonnet of
ultimate aroma!
Whoa!
Dude! The duck mixed
with all the spices...
[AOKI &amp; SATO]
I'm losin' it man!
(Yuki sniffing)
For his spices he's using
coriander and fennel, oregano,
and I don't know what
that is.. um...
Ah! It's so complex
that I can't get IT!
How could he have possibly
created such a splendid aroma
from such a young chef?
Spicy yet mellow
at the same time.
And rich though slightly sweet.
Soon he'll show us who is
the real king in the
kitchen around here.
This time and place
belongs to the god of AROMA!
(Crowd cheers)
[TAKI]
Hm? The heck's up with him?
What happened to the drive
he had a minute ago?
Perhaps the cheers
for his opponent
have driven him to
withdraw a bit?
He doesn't even hear
any of those cheers.
Right now, Ryo's senses
are focused purely on
the sear of his protein
and the sound of
the fat as it pops.
He's only taking in
what lies in that frying pan.
Measuring the weight of
the eel as it cooks.
[RYO]
All my senses are
at full throttle.
It's critical I stay
focused on what is cooking
right in front of me.
Come on. Come on...
(Fat pops)
Now! It's done!
Sure enough, Ryo looks to be
going with a matelote.
What's a Matelote?
It's a way of cooking fish by
simmering it in a wine sauce.
Ohhh...
[SOMA]
Wait up!? Didn't he already
break down that eel before?
Why's he putting it
back together?
That was after
he wrapped it.
He's cooked it after
encasing it in crepine
to restore its natural shape.
Hey isn't crepine caul fat,
that netting that's around
the stomach of animals
like cows and sheep?
[ALICE]
Yes. The fat adds
more depth of flavor
and gives the dish
a definite impact.
This dish is an
old classic for Ryo.
[ERINA]
Piping‐hot mashed potatoes...
accompanied by
handmade brioche.
He's playing a wealth of cards
in order to overwhelm
his opponent.
That is the kind of
explosive power he has
built his cooking on.
[RYO]
No matter how much you
play up the aroma
and use it like some kinda
lame performance art...
It won't matter.
I'm gonna eat you alive!
(Eagle screech)
(Ryo gasps)
I have some aces up
my own sleeve, as well.
Also, it doesn't matter
what cards you're holding
for you have to know how to use
them to their fullest extent!
Usually Akira's so calm, but...
...he's like a whole
different person.
To this point there's been
no need to bear his claws,
but now they're fully extended.
And look at him. He's smiling.
(Ryo grunting)
I'm finished.
[URARA]
Akira is the first
to unveil his dish!
The venue is already enveloped
in a rich aroma permeating
all the senses!
[AKIRA]
I present to you a duck Apicius.
[SONOKA &amp; TAKI]
Oh!
It's an ancient Roman dish...
favored by the Roman
gourmand Marcus Apicius.
[HINAKO]
The caramelized honey seems to
glisten vibrantly...
...and the spices coating
the duck's surface
give off their own aroma.
The aroma is
captivating my senses.
So, what happens
when I taste this?!
I can't even imagine! Oh!
Very well, time to taste.
(Surprised)
(Foodgasm moaning)
It's like a lavish bouquet...
running spices through
my whole body!
The aroma remains within...
even once you've chewed
and swallowed,
expanding throughout the system!
Oh! This is bliss!
It's an unbelievable
combination of scents!
This magical aroma is like...
[TAKI &amp; SONOKA]
an eagle's grip!
[GIN]
Upon the first bite, the spices
are what stand out most...
but there are
countless attributes.
The heat levels are moderate...
but it has a slight sweetness.
There is a cool,
refreshing sensation,
but also a pungent sourness.
This dish balances
all of these,
powerfully and skillfully.
It would be impossible without
his sense of smell!
Full‐scale attack!
[AKIRA]
Better dig your grave.
This aroma will surely
dominate your dish.
No matter how many
cards you may have...
they'll never be
a match for mine, Ryo.
Pay attention to
Ryo's eyes...
Huh?
[SOMA]
Watch, he's not dead yet.
Akira Hayama, I finally,
sense the fire of a
real challenge from you.
Otherwise, this fight wouldn't
have even been worth it!
[URARA]
And now, the challenger,
Ryo Kurokiba.
What kind of a trump card
will he be using to showcase
his specialty, seafood?
Now stick THAT in your face!
EEL MATELOTE!
Oh my! That certainly is a hefty
amount of food you've given us.
[SONOKA]
By using the crepine you've made
the juiciness of the eel
even more pronounced.
From the lack of aroma,
this is by far the loser.
Something so assertive is bound
to be just another regular‐
[RYO]
Quit your blah blah blah
and eat it lady.
It's getting cold.
WHAT'S THAT?
You bastard?!
I'll pound some friggin'
manners into you, for real!
[SONOKA] Taki please! Calm down!
If you think you can get away
with bein' an idiot 'cause
you're a student, think again!
Please just calm down a bit!
I'll show you some real beatin'
out back, you idiot!
And now, on with the tasting.
Lovely. It was slowly simmered
so it's nice and hot.
He marinated it with
red wine and cinnamon
before grilling it...
giving it a fresh
and bracing flavor.
That eel has gunpowder
hidden within its depths...
my own special incendiary
device that'll be sure
to blow you away!
Ahh!
[SONOKA]
What?!
[TAKI]
It's a fierce stimulus
that runs across the tongue!
What Ryo Kurokiba stuffed
his eel with is so...
Surprising!
It's plums!
He stuffed it with plums?!
For real?
Plums with eel,
are you kiddin' me?!
[SONOKA]
The fat of the eel spreads
across the tongue
along with the fruity
acidity of the plums,
dancing a dangerous dance.
The deliciousness of it
is a shot to the head!
Oh! I feel so numb.
You soaked plums in water
and put them in the eel...
which you wrapped in caul fat.
This must be what you were
talking about earlier.
You used plums as an explosion
of acidity, didn't you?
Just shut up and watch.
[RYO]
Next! Take your garnishes, the
brioche and mashed potatoes...
Drizzle 'em with that sauce
right there in front of you,
which is concentrated from
the umami of simmered eel.
Grab some of that eel
while your at it
and cram it in your mouth‐holes.
Go on and stuff your
eager judgey jowls...
until you can't fit any more
and want to puke it out.
[TAKI]
Dammit! This is Tohtsuki
Academy's celebration
of fine dining!
This guy needs to learn
some humility!
But...! (Gulp)
Okay, this is where the
gunpowder really goes off!
Target strike!
Mmm...
(Gasp)
[HINAKO]
The texture is enveloped
by the mashed potatoes...
[MIZUHARA]
...the fluffiness of
the brioche...
[SONOKA]
...and the sweet
fattiness of the eel
and the acidity of the
plums are going wild!
[HINAKO, MIZUHARA & SONOKA]
All come together
as one beautiful fusion!
[GIN]
This is different from
the bewitching flavor
of the first dish.
It's an explosion of focus,
sparing nothing as it
batters entire profiles
into sumptuous submission!
[TAKI]
Dammit! I can't resist!
I shrivel in his
dominating presence...
He's the predator
and I'm the prey!
[RYO]
You came here expecting
to win, didn't you?
Well I'm really sorry
about that!
(Gasp)
[URARA]
This concludes the tasting.
Next up, the judgment.
Please vote for which is
the superior dish!
This'll be settled soon.
But it...
...looks like the judges
are frozen!
All the other rounds seem to
have been decided instantly.
Even these veteran graduates
are having trouble
making a decision.
(Grunting in anticipation)
Hm...
I've decided! I think
I'm going with Akira Hayama!
(Grunts)
I'm voting for
Akira Hayama as well.
[CROWD VOICES]
That's two votes!
I don't believe it.
Is it a done deal?
So he won it after all.
Well, it was a perfectly
executed dish.
I'm choosing...
Ryo Kurokiba's eel dish.
But why would you?!
The depth of flavor he
achieved using seafood.
Amidst that maelstrom of manly
flavors fighting at the front,
I caught a glimpse of
true elegance!
I'd say it's a dish worthy of
being judged at the Final
Selection, wouldn't you?
Jeez!
[TAKI]
Which one?
Which should I choose?!
They both expressed themselves
so expertly with their
presented dishes.
But the one who made a more
forceful impression with
his cooking was...
Argh, dammit it all to hell!
I'm going with Ryo Kurokiba.
(Crowd gasps)
[Ryo] Hehehe...
This has just
turned out crazy!
Their opinions are
completely divided.
The average Food War's
never like this, bro‐chacho!
Yeah.
This will be decided by
whoever Chef Kikuchi picks.
I can't decide.
[CROWD]
Huh?
Both of their dishes
were splendid.
I can't pick, certainly
not one dish over the other.
Quit screwin' around
with my time!
(Sonoka screams)
This is a competition!
How can it end if someone
hasn't freakin' lost?!
Wrap it up, get it in gear!
(Sonoka scared)
What's the big deal!
Figure it out!
Get it together!
[MAN]
You're making a joke out of
a serious competition!
(Sonoka gasps)
Of course I can fully
understand her position.
That's how fiercely both of
them battled in here today.
I ask the members of
the committee!
We're right here Chef.
How can we help you?
What the? When did she... ?
Food War rules state that if
a decision cannot be reached
in the arena,
the battle should be
temporarily shelved
and then held again at a
later date. You're thoughts?
That is correct, Sir.
But this is the
Annual Fall Selection.
The attendees,
as well as the judges
are extremely busy
with other projects.
As you can well imagine, Sir.
I fear it would not be
realistically possible
to secure a date for
a rematch in time.
Which would be a shame.
Here's my suggestion then.
There is one way to get past
this immutable situation!
We allow them both
of them to advance.
This will be the first Fall
Selection in history...
to have three finalists
competing at the top!
I feel all three contestants
have shown they deserve it!
(Crowd gasps)
[GIRL]
Three finalists?!
[ERINA]
Still, this is
completely unprecedented.
For the decision to be
left to a single judge is‐
[SENZAEMON]
Agreed! Your suggestion
is intriguing!
(Gasp)
I say we endorse this.
As school director,
I allow this to move forward.
So now the battle between
Akira and Ryo is a decided draw.
Both move to the next round.
In the finals...
they will be joined by
Soma Yukihira...
to make three competitors
fighting it out!
(Crowd cheers)
(Group gasps)
[YUA]
Ryo Kurokiba,
congratulations on
making it to the finals.
So, uh, what do you think
of the competition...
What do you mean
"congratulations," you jackass?!
I don't accept any of this,
little girl!
They were too weak to
decide on a real winner.
This is bull craaaaap!
(Whistle blowing)
Ryo! Go back to the house now!
[AKIRA]
I must say it was upsetting...
It's rather irksome
that it had to end in
a stalemate with Ryo...
But I'm going to do my best.
I'll be sure to turn things
around for the next bout.
Hey, Master Soma Sir!
I hope you're able
to be as impressive
in the finals as well!
What? Yeah me too!
Oh man, this is kinda
awkward to do.
[SOMA]
So yeah, when I was with
those two in A Block during
the preliminaries,
I was one point behind Akira,
and I ended up tying with Ryo.
Yeah, my main focus was to
beat the both of them before
moving forward to the finals.
If I could have that chance...
it would totally be a bonus.
(Ryo growls)
(Akira grunts)
[URARA]
And so everyone, that marks
the end of the semifinals.
Next on the agenda,
the committee members
will announce
the theme for the
upcoming Fall finals.
Ohhh?
I love this part!
Every year the theme
presents a new Fall element.
No one knows what's coming!
That's what makes it so perfect
to decide the final
Fall Selection.
(Ice cracking)
[SATOSHI]
The theme is, Pacific saury!
In the past, it was
considered an inferior fish
that only commoners would deem
appropriate to eat.
But now high‐end restaurants
have been serving it.
And it's been showing up in
numerous restaurants overseas.
For the upcoming
Fall Selection finals
prepare a single dish
using Pacific Saury.
Akira Hayama.
Ryo Kurokiba.
Soma Yukihira.
Circumstances have left us
with three strong contenders.
I'm feeling a strange
sense of fate here.
Pacific saury has
a strong aroma...
It is part of the
revered seafood family...
and has deep ties
with the masses.
I present to you all...
an ingredient each of
the contestants can
showcase their strengths.
The finals are in 10 days.
I promise to you all, this
will be an unparalleled battle!
[JUN]
Akira dear!
There you are Akiraaa!
You made it!
I know I did, will you
pipe down already?
How can you be so calm
at a time like this?
As your teacher,
I'm so very happy for you!
Sorry, I'm gonna go
blow my nose!
[SOMA]
She's right, Akira.
You don't have to act all
calm around us, we all know.
You can show that
you're ticked off.
I have no reason
to be "ticked off."
What?
I'm continuing on,
my plans to make it to
the finals and gain victory
have been not been
affected in the slightest.
[RYO]
Ha! Our bout ended in a draw
and you're still trying to act
like you've got a chance,
you spice‐loving pretty boy?!
You're nothing but a one‐trick
pony who's only good at spices.
Remember I've seen your
whole deck of cards ponytail.
I'll get you next time.
You too, Soma Yukihira!
[ALICE]
What are you doing you goof?
We're going home.
Yeah...
If you'll excuse us.
[RYO]
Good job, guys.
[AKIRA]
Well look who suddenly
lost his conviction!
[SOMA]
I can't follow that
change in intensity...
[AKIRA]
See you later, Soma.
Have fun, while you still can.
Uh Mistress, can I challenge
you to a food battle
when we get back home?
Huh?
I'm still pretty amped up
after all that...
I'm not gonna be able to sleep
till the finals.
[AKIRA]
Hm. He thinks I'm only
good at spices.
[GIRL]
Today's semifinals
were awesome to watch!
(Gasp)
Huh?
(Girls gasp)
[AKIRA]
Fine. I'll show you,
Ryo Kurokiba.
You'll know the true
world of enticing aroma!
[SOMA]
The finals, huh?
I can't believe
I've finally made it here.
No, I'm just getting started.
Guess I'll go check it out...
the best view from
a place higher than this!
[NARRATOR]
Next Time:
"The Battle that
Follows the Seasons."