(Flute playing)
[GIN]
Verily I say unto thee...
it is as we step upon the final
battle at Gojo Ohashi Bridge!
Whereupon Benkei
grips his blade...
as does Ushiwakamaru.
And the battle begins!
[MIMASAKA]
Here's my twist!
[SOMA]
Hm...
(Students chatter)
[SATO]
I'm feeling kinda funny.
Think I'm melting.
[AOKI]
What's this awesome
smoky scent all over me?
[IKUMI]
It's bacon!
But if he's trying to
copy Soma's recipe,
shouldn't he be using
oxtail in his stew instead?
So then he's using
that bacon for...
[ERINA]
If he's adding bacon
to the beef stew,
then there's only one answer...
he plans to use it
as a garnish.
(Chuckles)
[MIMASAKA]
As you can see Soma...
Your recipe has no imagination
and is the type
that is strained.
The result is a plain dish
consisting of just
sauce and meat.
[ERINA]
And that's where an
essential ingredient
comes in to play...
the garnish.
Boeuf bourguignon...
a dish from Bourgogne
containing meat
simmered in wine
that's said to be
the original beef stew.
It has always
featured a garnish.
Croutons are most often used...
as are braised pearl onions...
sautéed mushrooms...
and crisp fatty bacon.
This smells so good
I can't stand it!
It's pretty mellow
but still manages
to pack a punch.
He used mesquite for his
smoking chips... nicely played.
It's a tree native to
the southern U. S.
often used for smoking,
though it hasn't really
spread to Japan.
In Texas, famous for
its barbecue,
it's one of the most beloved
smoking chips to use.
It has a sharp aroma to it...
and when used for
certain cuts of meat...
it can lend to them a
nice golden brown color.
I brined it first for juices...
then added simple spices
like sage, nutmeg, and
some bay leaves...
then came my
secret weapon...
brown sugar.
That will really draw out
the umami in this stew.
How does he know that?!
He knows as much as Shun
about smoked meat!
For the love of pork,
what is going on?!
I can't watch this!
Bastard...
[SONOKA]
What's he thinking?
Soma doesn't look like he's
adding any special garnish.
He probably thought
it was kind of unessential
like most people do.
Huh?
Unessential!
(Sonoka crying)
But when it comes to beef stew,
the garnish is an extremely
important ingredient
to consider.
The war is over.
There's no way Soma Yukihira
can win now.
You can't possibly assume that
without even tasting it.
That's no way to judge.
In a top kitchen,
a person like that
would just cause friction
amongst the rest of the
team trying to cook.
Shut up, you old bat.
I'm not even 30!
I'm still in my 20s
you young viper!
What's with that
damn voice of yours?!
Quit trying
to sound cutesy!
Tsunozaki, you should refrain
from discussing age so casually.
All right. Understood,
Miss Mizuhara ma'am.
Why do you only talk politely
to Mizuhara you beast?!
I choose who I respect
and who I don't.
[GIN]
His key ingredient of
oxtail was copied out
from under him...
and a specialty bacon
added to his own recipe.
For Soma Yukihira...
this is certainly
a dangerous situation.
What do you think
he should he do?
At this rate,
Soma's going to...!
Then if you win, I'll quit
being a chef and leave.
Please Master Soma Sir...
Oh? If it ain't
Mitsuru Sotsuda.
You should choose a stronger
password my little friend.
Your birthday is way
too easy to figure out.
Oh...
[MITSURU]
I'll write an
extra special editorial,
spreading the news of
Master Soma's Yukihira
marvelous victory!
You snuck a look at my upcoming
cover article, didn't you?
My job was made a whole lot
easier thanks to you.
Look forward to
the new story.
[MITSURU]
All those days Soma
spent on his dish...
The time he spent thinking
and perfecting everything.
Just to have it stolen.
And it's my fault!
(Gasp)
[MITSURU]
What's that?
Master Taki Tsunozaki...
is that correct ma'am?
[TAKI] Huh?
It looks like you've been
talking your mouth off
about me lately.
I'll listen to your
complaints lady...
AFTER I've presented
my food to you all!
That looks like...
...various...
...cuts of...
...meats!
He has cheek!
And tongue!
Honeycomb!
Tenderloin.
Please, if you will judges.
I'll soon be taking you...
to an Amusement Park of
Delicious Meat Glory!
[SOMA]
The tongue's been boiled
for a few minutes...
Time to remove the skin!
He's fast.
[SOMA]
To give it a good sear...
I need to fry it in some
mild butter and a dose of
refreshing olive oil.
The cheeks are marinating
in red wine with
celery stalks and bay leaves.
Season with salt and
black pepper...
give it a light dust
of flour and cook!
Next, place the pot with the
tenderloins in the oven.
Huh? What is this?
What's going on?!
It looks like he's making
something up right on the spot.
Impromptu cooking!
Where's the skirt steak?
(Gasp)
What the...?
Did he friggin' run off?!
(Gasp)
And he's back.
Well... hehe...
I'm glad I brought that charcoal
grill to the waiting room.
Beef stew using
a charcoal grill?
What does he think
he's doing down there?!
Is he just now putting it
together on the fly?
Well Soma, I get it.
So you turned out to be
THAT type of cook, huh?
There are only two routes
someone who knows about my
perfect copies can take.
There's pattern 1...
Bluffing until they launch
a surprise attack...
announcing what they'll
make ahead of time...
then shifting gears
and making something
completely different.
But guys who are confident
in their skills
tend to go with a
different approach...
I call this Pattern 2.
Impromptu cooking...
a way of battling out
with a perfectly clean slate
to try and work against me.
They've got nothing in mind.
Even so, most chefs
have panicked and lost
without being able to
bring forth a finished
dish to the judges.
But I bet you'll be able to
come up with something, Soma.
You're not the type
to lose your cool midway.
Well look at you?
You're actually
complimenting me?
'Cause I'm relying on just that.
I know everything
about you boy...
including how you went to
Aldini's apartment this morning.
And how after that...
I watched as you stocked up
on a bunch of specialty meat.
All right. We will begin our
judging with Subaru Mimasaka's
beef stew.
[MIMASAKA]
Go ahead...
Time to eat up! Oooo...
So for your garnish, you
chose to use smoked bacon,
mushrooms, and oignons glacés.
Incidentally, glacés means
"frozen" in French.
Did you know that already?
Anyway, I think their
glistening sheen gives
your dish a delightful little‐
Shut up and
eat already will you!
[SONOKA]
W‐well, here it goes.
Ahh...
(Gulp)
Mmmm...
[SONOKA]
The juicy thickness
of the oxtail
combined with the
mellowness of the white miso
is simply exquisite!
I feel like my tongue
could melt right off me!
[TAKI]
What's more, the scent of the
mesquite in the bacon packs
a real punch to the throat!
This is unbelievable!
I read all your moves,
even being impromptu.
That's the reason for
this added bacon.
I let it age in my special brine
for the last five days.
Then just to add
insult to injury.
I left it out in the wind,
letting it dry for a full day
before smoking it
for five full hours.
That's how I was able to
make it so flavorful...
'cause I spent
all that time on it.
That's true enough...
rather than muddling
the impact of the beef,
the umami of this
slow‐prepared pork
elevates it to a
whole other dimension.
The time and effort
this took is palpable!
It has a refined power,
the exact opposite of
impromptu cooking!
This is how Takumi's match
went down as well!
He even tried improvising,
but it's not going
to be enough...
His every move
ended up
being read.
He was one‐upped
by a moron!
It's just like Heaven!
So soft! So tender!
This flavor goes way beyond
just a simple copy.
(Crowd cheers)
[GIN]
This is like...
(Bell ring)
shooting sparks of flavor
as meat battles meat,
wrestling against each other
in the ring!
It's a dreadnought of
deliciousness
rippling through a body
of blossoming doom!
[SONOKANA]
No! I can't take it anymore!
(Screams)
[GIN]
The beef and pork combine...
...in a mouth‐watering
explosion!
(Crowd cheers)
[BOY]
They're all up in that meat!
I don't believe it!
He even wowed those pro chefs!
(Mimasaka laughs)
Looks like you had the
wrong idea, there Soma.
You trusted in
blind inspiration
to make a dish
right on the spot.
Mark my words boy...
That's nothing more
than your brain
being at a standstill.
When it comes to cooking boy...
the devil is always
in the details.
Whoever preps the most
will always win the most!
You can come up with as many
tricks as you want Soma...
but it's always pointless.
Pointless!
UTTERLY POINTLESS!
You should burn
this rotten day
into your memory.
For it will be the last dish
you ever serve in your life,
Soma Yukihira!
(Hiss)
(Mimasaka laughs)
(Soma laughs)
That's some pretty pathetic
talk there, Mimasaka.
You're not the only one
relying on things.
I was relying on you too.
[MIMASAKA] What the?
I've thought about you
this whole week.
Trying to piece together
were you were hiding
and what you were up to.
Huh?
[MIMASAKA]
What's he tryin'
to pull over me?
I should've accounted
for everything. So what...
what am I afraid of?
[SOMA]
Well, here you are.
(Scared cry)
Your order is up...
Yukihira‐style beef stew...
Fall Selection Special!
(Gasp)
He used different cuts of meat!
[ERINA] Hmm...
[EIZAN] Huh...
You're not screwing around
with us, are you?
I'm never seen any beef stew
like this before‐
[SOMA] What are you saying?
Have you never seen
beef stew before?
After all, they're all
considered a garnish.
[TAKI] What's that?!
Did he say they're
all garnishes?
The charcoal grill
gives it a rich aroma!
It looks like it's simmered
to absolute perfection.
[GIN] Hmm...
[MIMASAKA]
Ha! Looks like a bunch of
different ingredients
all thrown together.
This thing is a jumbled mess.
There's no way it'll
come close to the beauty
that my garnish
bestowed upon the world.
My bacon was aged with the
alluring aroma of smoked
sizzling mesquite.
The flavors were carefully laid
out to enhance each component!
Soo, the stew itself is
pretty much the exact same
as the previous
presented dish.
As for the garnish...
Hmm...
(Hinako screams)
[TAKI]
Help me!
Right!
Left!
And an unexpected
twist ramming into me!
OH GOD!
(Worried gasp)
The cheek meat is
so tender and juicy
that it practically
melts when you chew it.
The texture of the tongue and
the honeycomb is a lap fest of‐!
(Joyous screaming)
The grilled skirt steak
was sliced thick...
so the amount of juices
flowing out of it
is something else
entirely new!
When paired with the stew,
it accentuates into a bounty
of splendid loveliness!
Well, it looks like it's
thrown in carelessly at first,
but each cut was
prepared perfectly.
An expertly built
thrill ride of flavor.
Such a menagerie
achieving perfect balance.
Impossible! How is that?
How's that created on the fly?
[SOMA]
To tell you the truth...
I had the same ideas
as you obviously had.
I thought to boost the flavor
by using a powerful garnish
like smoked bacon, as well...
But I knew that
wouldn't work for me.
It's not my style of cooking.
So then I came up with
the idea of trying to combine
various flavors and ingredients
into one single dish.
(Gasp)
To think, you were able to
make such layers of flavor
using just a beef stew.
Actually, I just used
the thinking behind
a popular dish that I like
as a model for this.
"A popular dish"?
Yeah, it finally hit me right
in the head this morning.
The Chikuzenni dish.
[Both]
Huh?!
It's usually thought of as just
a simple simmered stew,
but chikuzenni made by a pro
turns out to be a bit different.
Right, Master Hinako?
Yes! Simmer time varies
according to each of the
different vegetables...
so that the color and flavor
is expressed fully in each.
Allowing each ingredient
to shine through.
Then at the very end,
they're all rearranged
into a single dish,
taking care to achieve optimal
balance between everyone.
The same goes for this dish.
That's certainly true,
chikuzenni has a
wealth of flavors.
That is so Soma
I can't stand it!
Damn you to hell Soma!
You fooled me all along, you
weren't winging it after all!
I never once told you
that I was, Mimasaka.
I've been putting this
entire thing together...
this whole time.
It's the ultimate
combination of everything...
of all the paths and flavors
I've walked and
experimented with.
I drew on all of that
extra knowledge,
piecing them together
in one single place.
Seeing as how you only ever
wanna steal your opponent's dish
and only bother to take that
one step needed to beat it,
I thought this would be
something you couldn't copy.
[MIMASAKA]
He's in a place my
perfect copies can't reach!
I don't know how to fight this!
[MIZUHARA]
What he's created is a paradise
that showcases the dazzling
deliciousness of meat.
[HINAKO]
It's a place of dreams
in which you'll always
want to be immersed!
[GIN]
I love you all!
(Judges giggling)
(Happy music)
[ALL]
Yukihira Land!
(Girls screaming)
(Gin laughing)
(Sonaka scared)
(Camera snaps)
Hey. Um.
About today...
let's never forget
about this, okay?
Yeah!
[ALL]
We will all be...
friends, forever!
(Gasp)
Let go of me, dammit!
But Taki, your hands
are so tiny and cute.
I just want to
play with them.
Back off!
What's with those glistening
eyes peering into my soul?!
Soma Yukihira's
something unique.
His mind never
stopped creating.
There are numerous
footprints left behind...
by always exploring
one's cooking.
That is nothing less than
the mark of an expert chef.
Soma Yukihira showed us
the perfect example of this
with his single serving
of beef stew.
Everyone we will now...
move to the judging!
For the first round of
the semifinals for
the Fall Selection,
also doubling as a Food War.
Judges please grab yours brushes
and cast your votes now!
Now then, what will
be the verdict?
It's unanimous!
Soma Yuikhira wins
against Subaru Mimasaka!
He now moves on to the finals!
You're welcome!
(Crowd cheers)
He did it!
Amazing!
Hmph!
[MIMASAKA]
It can't be...
There's no way you could
get past my brilliant
friggin' copying!
[SOMA]
If that's what you think...
then why not try a bite of
my winning beef stew?
(Trembling breath)
(Glup)
Ahhhh!
Yukihee Land.
(Clown laughing)
Damnit, it feels so good!
I don't ever want to
leave this place.
I'm starting to remember...
what happened not long after
I started cooking.
Don't make me go back.
[MAID]
You really are quite gifted
in the kitchen, young Subaru.
I can't believe you can
recreate any food you want
just by glancing
at the recipe.
You're definitely your
father's son all right.
You have such
splendid talent!
Stop you're embarrassing me.
I mean I'm just trying to learn
by the example my father set.
I, uh, sure hope he likes it?
I want him to be proud of me.
[MIMASAKA'S DAD]
Don't be happy
over some cheap copy!
To a true chef, nothing is
more important than
his own originality!
Cooking that lacks conviction
has no place here!
[MIMASAKA]
A few days later, there was an
important fair being produced
that would introduce
new dishes, one attended
by several VIPs.
I meant no ill will, I just
wanted a bit of praise.
I took one of my dad's
specialties
and by making one simple change
I was able to beat him.
(Dad grunting)
[MIMASAKA]
So he kicked me out.
Hehe... No, that's not it...
My father turned his back
and walked out on me.
Come on! Cooking is easy,
winning is even easier.
Just one step...
All it took was one extra step
to beat my opponent.
And I knew I had that skill!
As you can see....
All the elites of the greatest
cooking school in Japan
all failed helplessly, falling
to their knees in horror.
"First‐rate," my foot!
What does "conviction" matter?
You so‐called chefs are
disgrace to the profession!
Subaru Mimasaka,
I could use a guy like you.
Acknowledge only me and
I'll let you wreak devastation.
[KAGEURA]
With the conclusion of
this Food War...
Subaru Mimasaka has lost
the rights to keep claim
on all these utensils...
All are present.
Soma Yukihira, stated in full
all these will be returned
to their rightful owners,
is that correct?
Sounds awesome.
(Cheering)
[OIZUMI]
Ahh... A hundred knives are
going back to their rightful
chefs to be wielded once again.
[GIRL]
Um, excuse me! Soma?
Oh?
Thank you...
This was given as a memento
when my mother passed away.
It means everything to me.
Thank you very much.
I'm forever in your debt.
Hmph.
I guess the time has come...
I'll be leaving
Tohtsuki's Academy.
And I promise
not to cook anymore.
I acted shamefully,
and bore the embarrassment.
There's nothin' left for me
to be proud of any‐
Oof!
You dummy!
If you do that,
then there was no point
in me accepting
this Food War!
Huh?
Hey, what's wrong?
Aren't you gonna get it?
This last one left
is yours, Takumi.
Go grab it.
(Gasp)
[MIMASAKA]
Aldini!
Hm...
[TAKUMI]
Subaru Mimasaka...
I lost my challenge to you.
Completely.
But...
Next time, I WON'T lose!
If you move one step forward,
I'll move two...
no... I'll move ten
or even a hundred!
Things do not end like this!
Got it, Mimasaka?!
My mezzaluna is yours
to keep for the moment.
But one day I'll get it back...
once I've beaten you
in a Food War.
Hold onto it till then.
[SOMA]
Hehe...
Hear that...?
Anyone worth being a pro chef
can't stand losing.
You should pay closer attention
to what you're about to learn.
Listen closely, Mimasaka:
I'm just going to
tell you this once.
Don't ever think you can
wipe out someone's pride
with a single battle.
All the confidence you
so tirelessly built up...
Even if you suffer a loss that
tries to wash all that away...
Or a memory so terrible it
feels like you can't recover...
You can't quit.
You absolutely
MUST open up shop.
That's what makes
a true chef after all.
And you're like that too.
Never forget that.
[MIMASAKA]
I can't believe
he's actually tellin' me
to keep on cooking,
to keep on fighting.
(Mimasaka and clown laughing)
[MIMASAKA]
My heart, which was
wound hard and tight...
is starting to flow free!
I glisten freely!
Like the cuticles
of a young girl...
(Girls gasp)
[IKUMI]
He bet that he'd stop cooking
just to show that if you lose,
you can always just pick
yourself up and try again?
Well, that doesn't
make a lick of sense.
Hehe...
That sounds right.
That's just like Soma.
[SOMA]
Yo, Erina. I've managed
to make it this far.
Reaching the top spot
among the 1st years
and getting a chance
to take you on...
is just ONE step away!
Don't fool yourself.
I'm so far above you
it's not even possible.
[ERINA]
Also...
you still haven't brought me
that manga you owe me.
[SOMA]
Huh?
[URARA]
Now then folks,
time to move on to the second
round of the semifinals!
(Crowd cheers)
Facing off will be...
Ryo Kurokiba and
his opponent Akira Hayama.
[NARRATOR]
Next time:
"Beasts that Devour Each Other."