Sorry, but I overslept
this morning and ran
out of time.
So it's omelet rice again.
Y‐You know, I don't need
to bring lunch anymore.
Oh? Really? Why is that?
Well, most of the guys don't
bring their own lunches.
They all go to the cafeteria.
I'm going to be eating
with them from now on.
[sighs] Too bad.
I like to make your lunch.
But, since I made it today,
I want you to take it with you!
Uh, sure.
[Yu thinking] There’s no way I'd
be able to eat omelet rice
with a message written on it
in a classroom.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
‐[Takajo] Oh, good morning.
‐Yeah, good morning.
You seem fairly spiritless
today.
No, this is about how low
my spirit is all the time.
Especially mornings.
Tell you what: at lunch today,
I'm gonna buy you
the limited edition
beef tongue curry,
guaranteed to lift your spirits
right up.
Will you make it there in time
to get a limited edition?
With my ability for speed,
it'll be a piece of cake.
Ah, that's right.
[bell tolls hour]
[whoosh!]
[muffled moaning, clatter]
[Yu groans]
Huh?
Hello, I've been
waiting for you. Here you go.
[Yu] Right now, I think
it would be better if we got you
straight to the hospital.
Oh, I'm used to this.
It happens all the time.
I'm sorry to make you
worry about me.
[Yu] His ability
is way too half‐assed.
Ahhh! A flood of spices.
This is how curry should be!
Delicious!
I'm glad it exceeds
your expectations.
Curry is something that should
be spicy, after all.
[Takajo] It's medium spicy,
but is that the right level
of spice for you?
The beef tongue melts
in your mouth.
It's the best!
‐[Takajo] You must
really love curry.
‐Mm‐hmm.
I'd actually forgotten
how much.
[buzz]
OK. I understand.
Our comrade is coming again.
We should head
to the student council room.
[crash!]
[wet footsteps]
Why does that guy always
show up soaking wet?
He can't use his special ability
unless he gets soaking wet
while fully clothed first.
[Yu]
What a cumbersome,
half‐assed ability.
The ability is channeling.
‐What is "channeling"?
‐Spiritualism.
Allowing dead individuals
to possess them like shamans.
Someone who can really
use that as a special ability
and not just a fraud?
That’s pretty amazing.
One more: pyrokinesis.
[gasp]
I can't believe this person
has two abilities.
I'd like to get moving and grab
this one as quickly as possible.
Wait, this is an ordinary road.
And is that
supposed to mean something?
‐It means they're on the move.
‐In the middle of a weekday?
Are they ditching school
or something?
But this road is troubling.
It'd be much better if
it wasn't a narrow alley
that's not very popular.
So, what’s the big deal?
Oh, well, we should
head out there anyway.
[snarls]
‐Huh? This is the place?
‐Yes.
What's the matter?
It looks like that person
must have been pretty desperate
‐when they passed through here.
‐How's that?
[Tomori] This side of the box
has no dust on it.
In other words, whoever it was
ran through here
and bumped into this box.
[Takajo] What you're saying is
that you think this person
was being chased.
Sounds like there was
an incident.
‐Another troublesome‐‐
‐For now we'll keep
moving forward.
[Tomori] Two new sets
of footprints.
One of them
has a short stride
and the other one
is quite a bit longer.
This totally indicates a girl
being chased by an adult.
We have to hurry.
‐Oh, that thing earlier?
‐[Tomori] What was it?
They were filming something
where an idol was being chased
by a big guy.
‐[Tomori] An idol?
‐Let's see...
Right, it was Yusa Nishimori.
‐I've heard that name before.
‐[Yu] Me too.
‐[fanfare plays]
‐Yusarin?!
[Yu] Oh, yeah.
It's the idol that Ayumi likes.
‐So you know her?
‐She's the unbelievable
lead vocalist
for the band How‐Low‐Hello
and an upcoming gorgeous
super idol
that sings and dances
like no one I've ever seen
in my life!
I can't tell you what
a big turnoff that is. Stop!
Her career started
in the sixth grade when
she won the grand prize
in the 14th
reader‐model audition
for the magazine Petit Banana
and debuted
as their exclusive model!
Then she landed a job
as a regular member of
the "Movement Morning!" show
but quit two years later
to focus on school.
She restarted her career
in show biz after‐‐
Hold it.
Let's get back to the point.
So that girl caused some issue
with her special ability
and became a fugitive,
am I wrong?
‐You really don't have
to say that for us to know it.
‐[Yu groans]
[Yu] Her agency
is Sea Rex Productions.
Wouldn't it be quicker
if we just called them?
‐We're talking show biz here.
They're not gonna tell us
anything.
Then what should we do?
[Tomori] Let's see.
[gasp]
A suspicious target.
I'll chase him!
‐[Yu] Tomori!
‐Otosaka, use your ability!
[Yu] Huh?
[energy pulses]
[groans]
[Yu moans]
I'm the one who actually
feels the pain,
so I'd rather you not
use this tactic from now on.
‐This is why
we get compensation.
‐What?
[groans] That hurt.
Damn it, what would you have
done if the camcorder broke?
[Yu] That's your issue?
[Tomori] Wake up, bastard.
[suspect groans]
[Tomori] Who the hell are you?
No, who the hell are you?
Tell us what we wanna know
and we'll call
an ambulance for you.
You realize you're headed
straight to death right now?
I was just offered a job,
all right?
[Tomori] What kind?
Sorry, I can't tell you that.
Is it something you're willing
to lose your life to protect?
[suspect] I'm looking
for Yusa Nishimori.
[Tomori] And who asked you
to do that?
[suspect] Taiyo TV.
Right. What was their name?
I don't know the person's name.
And that's the truth.
Great, understood.
I'd already called for
an ambulance before you talked.
[siren wails]
[stranger] Hey.
What the hell are you guys?
Just some people looking for
a woman named Yusa Nishimori.
Her nickname is Yusarin!
Why are you looking?
I don't exactly know
the reason why,
but it's a fact that
she's being chased, so we
thought we'd help her out.
‐You guys know Yusa?
‐I'm a huge fan!
‐[kick]
‐Would you stop interrupting?
I was watching you.
How the hell did you
defeat that guy?
[Tomori] We did it
using special abilities.
Probably a lot like the ability
Nishimori has.
[stranger] How do you know
about that?
If you just trust us, I believe
we can help save her from harm.
I see. I'm gonna need
to see some proof.
Show me that you have
the same power that she does.
It's not exactly
the same power, but...
What the...?
[Tomori] Here.
Now do you believe
what I'm saying?
Yeah. Come on,
I'll take you to her.
‐Though it's a bit confusing.
‐[Tomori] What do you mean
by that?
Things got slightly complicated.
I want you guys
to see for yourselves.
[Tomori] So this
is a nightclub.
[Yu] You really don't
have to film all this, do ya?
[stranger] This way.
And don’t lag behind.
Hey, I'm back.
So how is everything
outside today?
Ohh! It actually is
the real Yusarin!
‐I have all
the How‐Low‐Hello CDs.
‐Big turnoff!
Thanks so much,
that's wonderful.
[Yu] It really is
the girl I saw on TV.
Hey, what is with those guys?
They're just like Misa
and have special abilities
that they can use.
Wait a minute, I thought
her name was Yusa,
but it's actually Misa?
That's the part
that makes this complicated.
What are you doing?
You sure we can trust them?
I watched them use their powers
to defeat those other guys,
all right?
Is it OK if we ask her directly
what's going on here?
If you ask something stupid,
you're not getting out of here
in one piece.
[Yu] Why you gotta be so scary?
Tomori, be really careful here.
Yeah, yeah.
It's very nice to meet you.
I'm Tomori.
I'm Yusa Nishimori,
nicknamed Yusarin.
It's very nice to meet you.
[Yu] So she
calls herself Yusarin?
This is the first time in
my life I've met a real idol.
You're so unbelievably cute,
you almost look like a doll.
‐I want to get as close
to you as she is.
‐Hey, back off!
Now, now.
So first off, could you please
tell me your actual name?
‐It's Yusa Kurobane.
‐Yeah? Well, I wasn't
asking you!
[Yu] Your real name sounds
more like a stage name.
Yes. I hear that a lot.
But Kurobane means
"black feathers,"
and it's not really suitable
for an idol,
so they renamed me Nishimori.
That makes sense.
Now, there are some occasions
when you are not
Yusa Kurobane.
Are you aware of that fact?
No, she's not, so how do you
know about it?
‐I wasn't asking you, bastard.
‐What was that?
So, was I right about that,
Kurobane?
That's exactly it.
I guess you can call it
sleepwalking.
I've been falling asleep
without realizing it,
and then when I wake up,
I'm somewhere else,
with no idea how I got there.
The doctors who examined me
said there's a chance
that I have
a multiple personality disorder.
Oh, they did, huh?
Well, it's not schizophrenia,
so you don't have to worry
about that.
[sighs]
She has her own special ability
just like the three of us.
Her power is
to allow a dead person
to possess her body.
Seriously?
I believe that the ability is
calling forth this Misa girl
that you guys
were talking about earlier.
‐[Yusa] Misa?
‐[Tomori] Is something
the matter?
‐[Kota] Don't ask anything.
‐Is it someone she knew?
Yeah, she was Yusa's
older sister.
She died six months ago
in an accident.
You bastard.
Don't go blabbing on
about things
to some stranger
you just met!
‐[Takajo groans]
‐Can I assume that you're Misa?
It's so annoying how cramped
it is with all of you here!
[Yu]
She’s totally changed.
‐[Tomori]
‐Whoa, that's really impressive.
[Sho] Calm down, Misa!
You're gonna burn us all
to death!
[Misa] I suppose
that wouldn't be good.
[Tomori] I'm very surprised.
It seems she can't call forth
the spirit on her own
and that Misa is in control.
So you got a problem with that?
[Yu] Another ability that's
somehow half‐assed.
That means she has
an unparalleled ability
to be possessed.
And Misa, who possesses Yusa,
has pyrokinetic ability.
Yeah.
So, what is your relationship
with these two?
They're my friends
from back when I was alive
and still causing trouble.
[Tomori] Do you have any idea
why your little sister
is being chased?
Yeah. 'Cause of this.
Yusa accidentally brought this
home from some shoot.
It belongs to one of
the bigger‐name producers
at the TV station.
And she accidentally read
a text that was sent to it.
Stealing company money,
organized crime connections.
Stuff that would get the guy
arrested if it was taken
to the cops.
[Tomori] Did you guys think
to turn the power off?
Yeah. But it was on
until yesterday.
[Tomori] Then they probably
already know
that you're hiding somewhere
in this area from the GPS.
Even if you gave
the phone back now,
you wouldn't be safe.
And, if you gave it
to the police,
it would look like Kurobane
sold out the producer
and could keep her
from working in show biz.
OK, I'll burn it down,
station and all.
Are you stupid? You do that,
and your little sister
will end up in prison!
Who the hell do you think
you are, huh?
Do you really want to do
something that will land her
a stint in juvenile hall?
That would make
absolutely no sense.
[Tomori] Now please calm down.
You want to save your sister,
right?
Huh? Yes, of course.
Then we should help each other
turn the tables on this guy
and threaten him instead.
Huh?
Can we win?
I'm really good at creating
wonderfully devious plans
for threatening others,
so you can trust me.
You've got spunk.
All right then,
I'll do whatever you say.
I'd like the both of you
to help as well.
[Sho] Of course we will,
if Misa says so.
Oh my, I didn't fall asleep
again just now, did I?
You must be really tired,
that's all, it's all right.
Why don't you have some
roasted marshmallows and relax?
[Yusa] Oh!
The marshmallows turned
into freshly roasted ones.
[Takajo thinking]
This is unbearable.
I have no clue how I should
approach Yusarin from now on.
Every picture I had in my head
about her has been blown.
[Yu]
You're a scary guy.
First we should head to a shop
that sells work clothes.
‐What for?
‐You two are going to need
a set of fireproof clothing.
[vibrates]
[line rings]
‐[click]
‐[producer] It's me.
Huh?
So you finally showed up.
Realize that you couldn't
escape?
[Yusa] Um, I really don't know
the reason why I'm being
chased so much.
Did I do something wrong?
[producer] Give me back
my phone!
‐Is this the one?
‐[producer] Yeah.
Even if I return it to you now,
am I, like, still in trouble?
Whatever happens,
there's no future for you
in this industry anymore.
There's no more future for me?
Bastard! The one who has
no future is you!
[groaning]
I think I'll take out one more!
What the...
What the hell's going on?
You probably thought that
you had me cornered tonight,
but you didn't realize that it
was me that had you cornered
all along.
You really are senseless,
you know?
[producer] What the hell
are you?
I mean, are you really
Yusa Nishimori?
Of course, I'm Yusa Nishimori,
the real Yusarin, who else?
And in order to ensure
my success,
I'm willing to kill anyone
who gets in my way, like them!
[screams] That hurts!
This is getting boring.
I'll get rid of them
all at once.
W‐Wait, wait, wait.
Just a minute. Hold on, please.
‐Like I'm gonna wait!
‐[producer groans]
What the hell is going on here?
[Misa] I can bury you
in the shadows at any point
I want, understand?
I get it, I give up.
Please, don't hurt me.
[Misa] I'll give this
back to you.
But there is no next time.
I'll eradicate you
in a heartbeat.
[producer whimpering]
[both snicker]
[Tomori] Thank you very much
for all your help.
[Misa] No, you helped us.
He believed that everything
that happened tonight
was done by Yusa
all on her own.
That producer will never dare
to go up against her again.
No, I'm afraid everything is not
completely settled yet.
And so I'd like you to transfer
into Hoshinoumi Academy
and do everything you do
alongside us from now on.
Why would she do that?
Just like how
I explained earlier.
If she gets caught
by the scientists, her days
as a guinea pig will begin
and she will never be able
to return to a normal life,
understand?
The condo next to our academy
will be the safest place
for Kurobane to continue to grow
and live something
of a normal existence.
[Misa] That's a life‐saving
story for Yusa.
We'll do that.
Hold on!
Then, well...
If Yusa's powers disappear,
does that also mean
we'll never see Misa again?
Yeah, that's exactly
what I wanted to ask.
Well, I suppose
that will happen,
but she's already dead,
isn't she?
Isn't it amazing that you were
able to see her at all?
‐But‐‐
‐Sho, it's just like she says.
In reality, she's not here.
It's time to say goodbye
and let her go.
Then at least let me tell her
how I truly feel about her.
[Misa] Hmm?
Well, uh...
How do I put this?
Now is when I can't
think of what I should say?
Huh? Sho? Did you used to have
the hots for me?
Uh...
That's right.
I really loved you, Misa.
It's embarrassing to say...
but I was in love
and you passed away
before I could tell you.
We had a motorcycle accident
while we were riding together.
I was OK, but I was the one
that killed you.
It's my fault.
I see. It's all right.
I made you harbor
such immense feelings inside,
but I was the one that looked
for dangerous thrills.
I reaped what I sowed.
Don't cry,
that's not like you at all.
Sho, forget about me.
And starting tomorrow,
live your own life.
And don't keep dragging
the dead into it.
Otherwise, your life
will get screwed up
and you won't be happy
in the future, OK?
Jeez, you really are
a troublesome boy.
Sho.
[Sho] All right, Misa.
I'll walk my own path
that you're not a part of.
I'll sever my feelings
for you.
And that's how I'll live on.
Good. And I hope
that both of you
live very long and happy lives.
‐Yeah.
‐Sure.
See ya!
And thanks for everything.
'Cause it was
absolutely great!
[Yu sighs]
[Yu]
It was a really long day.
I'm exhausted.
You are so late!
If you're going to be this late,
I told you that I wanted you
to call!
How about you?
What are you doing up
at this hour?
Eating dinner together
as a family is a rule
that's been passed down
the Otosaka house
for generations.
Sorry, I was busy again today
doing work for
the student council.
Aww. When you say that to me,
I can't say anything back.
So tell me, what is it you made
for dinner tonight?
I made a very satisfying
spaghetti with meat sauce.
[soft music in background]
Oh! It's How‐Low‐Hello again!
[giggles]
‐[sighs]
‐[woman singing in Japanese]
Wow, it really is the same
person that I met today.
Huh? Who exactly
are you talking about?
You know, Yusa Nishimori,
the actual person.
You mean the real one?
So you've actually gotten
to meet Yusarin?
[Yu] Oh, crap!
But they didn't tell me
to stay quiet about this.
So I guess I can tell her.
She's transferring
into my academy tomorrow.
What? Oh, that makes me
so jealous!
Do you think that maybe I'll be
able to meet her soon?
Well, I guess that certainly is
a possibility.
Wow!
‐Oh, wow.
‐Let's start by cleaning up
your nosebleed.
It's just something
that's so amazing!
[Yu] Come on,
you're getting way too excited
about this.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]