OK. Time to go.
Sis.
[door opens, shuts]
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
[girl] Good morning.
Ah! I'm so glad you're finally
back, Otosaka!
[Takajo] It's good to see you.
Thanks. Sorry it's been
so crazy. Uggh!
[various students] Just because
he's a little handsome...
Screw that jerk...
Can't believe this!
Hey, we get it.
There's really no need
for you to apologize.
Absolutely. We're just glad
to have the student council
back together again.
That's why I've decided
to stick with you
until this is through
and you're back to normal.
[Yusa] I have a gift
for you, Otosaka.
A magic spell
to celebrate your return.
What? It can't be!
[cheery music plays]
Now, everything is wonderful.
You just needed some time.
Now the past is in the past
and you're gonna be fine!
There it is!
The memorable Yusarin
Magic Spell series, number one!
It's the magic spell of...
you're gonna be fine!
The very first day of her show,
this infamous magic spell idea
dominated
the fortune‐telling segment!
Enough!
Hey, good morning, Yusarin.
I just reserved your new single.
I'm so excited!
‐I bought five copies.
‐I got six.
‐[Takajo] You poseurs.
‐[others gasp]
[Yu thinking] I'm actually
thankful for their annoying
cheerfulness.
Who'd have thought?
Makes me feel like
I can be myself again.
Come to think of it, I should
apologize to Shirayanagi
next time.
I was pretty awful to her.
About the new single...
Ta‐da! It's the music video
that comes with the first press
of my brand‐new single!
‐[all] I wanna see it!
‐[Tomori] Knock it off!
[Takajo] Meet you
in the cafeteria?
‐Yeah.
‐[whoosh!]
‐[Takajo groans]
‐[Yu] Here we go.
‐[bell ringing]
Here it is, nice and hot.
Enjoy.
You know, you didn't
have to go through this
just to welcome me back.
[Takajo] Don't read
too much into it.
I just had a craving for it.
I haven't had this limited menu
for a while myself.
[Yu] I can read him
like an open book.
But I shall appreciate and
accept his kindness for now.
I'm really glad
that I can have this again.
Thanks a lot.
[both] Time to dig in.
I forgot how good it was.
Right? No matter how many times
I eat this, it never gets old.
[phone vibrates]
We gotta go.
We'll have to scarf it down.
That guy is gonna show up again,
isn't he?
Jeez, you're slow.
What is your zodiac sign again?
[Yu] You always call
when we're eating!
[Tomori] Well, now that
everyone is here,
I guess we'll start by watching
Kurobane's music video.
‐[Yu] Huh?
‐I don't know,
I'm so embarrassed!
Ohh! All right!
I'll get to see it
before anyone else does!
Ha ha ha! Waaah!
Don't worry, Yusa.
Even if the video sucks
out loud,
someone here will still love it.
♪
♪ I can do it too
once I'm there with you ♪
♪ Hata kara byojaku de ♪
♪ I can do it too
once I'm there with you ♪
♪ Suki kirai ooi ♪
♪ I can do it too
once I'm there with you ♪
♪ Fura to kaeri hitori
ni naru ♪
♪ Saitei no Hatsunetsu
Friday! ♪
[Takajo moaning]
♪ Hitori kiri demo ♪
♪ Tsuyoku nareru ♪
♪ Sou omotta hi ga tooku
natteku ♪
♪ Kimi wa ima dokoni
irundarou ♪
♪ Nodo mo kawaki kitte ♪
♪ Koemo todokanai ♪
♪ I can do it too
once I'm there with you ♪
♪ Doko ni mukatterunda ♪
♪ I can do it too
once I'm there with you ♪
♪ Nani mo wakaranai ♪
♪ I can do it too
once I'm there with you ♪
[Yusa] Thanks for listening.
I really hoped you enjoyed it.
[Yu] Well, give her
some kind of feedback.
Haaaa...
Hey.
‐Huh. It's pretty good, I guess.
‐Huh?
Yusarin's so happy.
She got a compliment from you!
Well, now I'm docking points
since you spoke
in the third person.
[both gasp]
Out of curiosity, Tomori, around
how many points do I have total?
Ten for singing,
20 for the song,
20 for the costume,
30 for the editing,
and minus‐51 for the singer
being pathetic.
‐OK...
‐So that means she has...
A total of 29 points.
Huh? You just flunked Yusa!
But what would it be
if you scored it based
on the music video alone?
Around 80 points.
‐Yay!
‐That's much better.
All right,
Yusarin's so happy!
It just dropped down
to 19 points.
[screams]
But that score makes Yusa sound
like a total idiot.
Well, I suppose I could judge it
from a business standpoint.
In which case,
it's a perfect 100.
Really? That's pretty unusual
for you.
‐All right, I'm so happy!
‐Wow, you did it, Yusarin.
I wanna watch it again!
[Tomori] Fine.
But it's the last time.
♪ I can do it too
once I'm there with you ♪
[Yu] Jeez, what's taking
this guy so long?
Oh, he's not coming today.
[Yu] Huh? Then what did
you call us for?
Calm down.
It'll be worth it.
Voilà!
Uh‐huh. Let's see.
Looks like these are tickets
to a Zhiend concert.
And they're for
tomorrow night's performance.
What's "The End"?
I thought you would have
heard of them, Yusa.
Zhiend is the rock band
Tomori likes so much.
It's post‐rock.
Get it right, moron!
[Takajo] Uh, post‐rock?
Look it up on Wiki.
[Takajo] Now I'm even more
confused.
You don't have to understand it
to see them.
Look, I have two tickets to see
the greatest band ever.
You're here to help me figure
out what to do with them.
Wait, I don't get it.
What else do you do
with tickets?
I think she needs one of us
to take the second one.
Otherwise it's a waste.
Oh, I see.
But I don't know about
that something‐rock.
It sounds kind of bizarre.
[groans] Their reviews
and popularity overseas
are super high.
If your song was a perfect score
at 100 points,
Zhiend would score
a million easy.
Wait! You're saying their score
is higher than perfect?!
[Tomori] So, do I have
any volunteers?
Hmm... I don't have much
of an interest, honestly.
Guess you're taking
one for the team, Otosaka.
‐Huh? Why me?
‐That's perfect.
‐I think the two of you
will have a great time.
‐Wait!
You can't just decide by
process of elimination.
I know, why don't we ask Misa?
She'll probably dig it a lot.
Only if I can listen
to a super‐fast two‐bass
at 260 BPM.
You won't get a super‐fast
two‐bass at 260 BPM, so you
might as well forget it.
Looks like
it's all decided, Otosaka.
‐Enjoy the concert.
‐[Yu sighs]
[Yu] Can I afford
to indulge like this?
[Tomori] It's OK
every once in a while.
People do need breathers.
[Yu] All right, guess I'm going.
Uh, excuse me.
[Yu] A foreigner?
[woman, softly]
Why avoid me? Jeez!
[Yu gasps]
[Yu] What... was that?
It can't be.
Hey, wait. Do you...
understand me?
[woman] Take me somewhere
I can eat modern yaki, pronto.
[Yu] Uh, I'm sorry,
what did you say?
You got sand in your ears?
Mo‐dern ya‐ki, now.
‐Modern yaki?
‐You gotta be kidding.
Nobody seems to know.
What the hell is with Japan
these days?
Jesus!
[Yu] Are you talking
about okonomiyaki
with noodles in it?
Yes, noodles!
That's exactly what I want.
Is there a place nearby?
[Yu] If you don't mind it
being Hiroshima yaki,
you can find it
in any hole‐in‐the‐wall.
‐[woman] Does it have
noodles in it?
‐Uh, yeah.
‐[woman] Then let's get going!
‐All right, all right,
I'll take you there.
[waiter] Welcome.
‐One Hiroshima yaki.
‐And a medium draft beer.
Got it.
‐Not for me.
I'll have oolong tea.
‐[waiter] Rock on.
Oh, sorry, make that two
Hiroshima yakis.
[waiter] No problem.
Even if I go home,
nobody's gonna have dinner
ready for me anymore.
I have to get used
to this lifestyle.
Aaaah!
Man, that hit the spot.
You wanna cook it yourself?
Oh, actually, she's blind
so would you mind
cooking it for us?
Sure thing. Huh?
Hold on. This woman is blind?
No way. Are you...?
That's right,
the vocalist for Zhiend.
I'm Sala Shane.
[Yu] I knew it.
Wow! I can't believe Sala
dropped by
my filthy
little okonomiyaki shop!
I'm so excited
about the gig tomorrow.
Please, can I get an autograph
on a signboard?
[Sala] Sure. Love to.
‐[Yu] I'm surprised she can
write that without seeing.
‐Here you go.
You're the greatest!
And here's your food!
Eat up and enjoy!
Hmm.
[Yu] Is there a problem?
[Sala] Hmm...
The pancake's thin.
[Yu] I told you
it wasn't modern yaki.
There are going to be
differences.
Oh, right.
But it's still good.
Nothing less from Japan.
[waiter] Thank you very much!
Can't wait to see you rock it!
Sorry.
I was short on cash.
[Sala] Eh, it's whatever.
So, uh, did something bad
happen to you recently?
‐Huh?
‐The way you breathe and talk
says a lot on its own.
You've been oozing out despair
from the moment we first met.
I don't talk about it.
[Sala] If I had to guess,
I'd say you lost someone
very close to you.
You're amazing.
That's exactly it.
If you don't mind,
can you tell me about it?
[Yu] Just the other day,
I lost my little sister.
[Sala] Oh, my God!
You've gone above and beyond
for me.
The least I could do
is put up some smoke
for that sister of yours.
Put up smoke?
You mean burn some incense?
‐Yeah, incense.
‐No, you don't have
to go that far.
[Sala] Come on,
I'm begging you here. Please?
[Yu] All right, I get it.
Would you please quit bowing?
[Yu] Hey, I have a favor
to ask you.
[Sala] Hmm?
There's someone
I'd like you to meet.
They're siblings that really
love your band.
Huh. It sounds like
those friends of yours
aren't just ordinary fans.
Uh, no, not really.
Could you hold on just a second?
[Yu] I just realized
that this is
the first time
I've ever called her.
It feels weird.
[line ringing]
‐[Tomori] Tomori here.
‐Hey, it's me, Otosaka.
[Tomori] You're calling me?
That's weird.
Is something wrong?
OK, try not to freak out
too much when I tell you this,
but the vocalist for Zhiend
is in my house as we speak!
[Tomori] And?
Huh? What's the deal?
You don't believe me?
[Tomori] No, I believe you.
There's no reason
for you to lie.
So, what do you want?
You can meet her.
What would be the point
of that?
[Yu] Oh, I don’t know.
You can talk to her, interact.
Sure, but I wouldn't go
out of my way to do that.
Look, I love Zhiend's music
and stage presence,
so I just wanna listen to
their CDs and watch their gigs.
That's all.
[Yu sighs]
Is that really
all you called me for?
‐I'm hanging up.
‐No, that's not it!
You're trying my patience here.
What is it?
Thanks for waiting.
The person I'd like you to meet
is still a little far from here.
When do you have to be back by?
Time isn't really a factor, kid.
Don't worry.
Take me wherever you'd like
to go.
I know we only met
a few hours ago,
but what's important to you
is already important to me
at this point.
Are you sure that it's
all right?
I mean, your gig
is happening tomorrow.
[chuckles] The band members
and our producer
will just have to make do
somehow.
That helps a lot.
Thanks a bunch.
Oh, I have to tell her
I don't need dinner.
Oh, damn it.
I did it again.
She's not here anymore.
[sighs]
And with that heavy sigh,
I've officially lost count.
Did you remind yourself
of your little sister again?
Wow, you see through pretty much
everything, don't you?
Hey, I need food, stat.
What? How is it possible
you're still hungry?
That one was just lunch, silly.
Now it's time for dinner.
OK, do you have something
in mind?
After a relaxing train ride,
soba is the only choice.
Great God in heaven!
Croquet Soba is the most amazing
thing I've ever tasted!
Ahh! What miraculous chemistry!
I gotta pay my respects
to whoever came up with this.
I'm so happy for you.
[Yu] Hey, can I ask you
one thing?
[Sala] Yeah, of course you can.
Sorry if this is
a delicate question,
but your eyes,
are they 100% blind?
Yep. I can't see a thing.
But you can write autographs.
I'm assuming that means you
weren't born blind, were you?
No. But I've come to think of it
as my penance.
Wait, penance?
This is how I atone
for all my sins.
Have you ever thought about
the great tragedy of life
before?
That was
an abrupt change of topic.
[Sala] Life is something
you only live once, right?
[Yu] Of course.
[Sala] I had dreamed
of spending my life
working on stage
as the front man for a band.
But my life was already
beyond hope before I knew it.
And I couldn't grant myself
that dream.
I was pitiful at both
singing and playing guitar
and watched as people my age
were showered with praise
for their songs.
I hated God.
OK, but aren't you living
that dream right now?
‐Yes, but that's only because
I was able to cheat.
‐How so?
[Sala] How isn't important.
The fact is that I was greedy.
There was a time when I was
popular in Japan too.
A social phenomenon!
A person of the times.
That kind of success.
When you're making
the kind of money I was,
the people around you start
to look at you differently,
and always for the worse.
In the end, you even become
a threat to your family.
My little brother was once
kidnapped for ransom.
That's when I walked away
from the life.
After that, I decided
to be the front man
for a really dull band.
Finally, I bartered my eyesight
away to God,
and that's the end.
Why to God?
Well, who the hell else
was I gonna give it to.
Look, I don't expect you
to understand what I'm saying,
but one day, if you find
yourself in a similar situation,
make sure you handle it well.
[Yu] It's just
at the top of this hill.
I need you to walk
a little further, OK?
[Sala] All right.
Sorry about this.
I feel like a jerk,
dragging you all over the place.
What? Give yourself
some credit, kid.
You're a kind person.
That much I'm sure of.
But you weren't always
like this, now, were you?
Well, uh, never thought of it,
but you're probably right.
Sometimes people change us
for the better.
[Yu] My mind instantly turned
to Tomori at that thought.
So she influenced me?
[Tomori on phone]
You're trying my patience here.
What is it?
I want your big brother to meet
with Sala for a little bit.
‐Why?
‐Because he's a fan.
‐And he's been
into Zhiend's music forever.
‐And?
And then something might happen
if they meet.
Do I have to spell it out
for you?
What would happen?
[Yu] Come on.
He might become sane again.
That would never happen,
and you know it.
Maybe, but I'd still like
to believe it could.
[Tomori sighs]
[Tomori] I guess it's not
certain either way.
Go ahead and give it a shot.
[Yu] Thank you.
[Tomori] But why do you care
about my brother so much?
Well, I, uh...
[Yu thinking]
That's a good point.
I've always been
the kind of person
who looks out for himself.
[Tomori] Is something wrong?
Nothing.
Just a whim, I guess.
[Tomori] Huh. It's still weird,
but...
thank you very much.
Then can you let
the hospital know
that Sala and I should be there
sometime this evening?
Sure. No problem.
[Yu] I don't know what condition
he's in right now.
You might want
to steel yourself for this.
[Sala] Don't worry.
I can tell this is
some heavy stuff just by
the sound of your voice.
[screaming]
Damn it, the painkillers
wore off again.
I'm getting a very strange
vibe from this guy.
So, do you have any idea
what he's doing right now?
Uh, I think he's composing.
Really? This is a lot heavier
than I expected.
He was a big fan
of your band in the past.
He was about to make
his debut as a guitarist
for a major label.
[Sala] I see.
[screams continue]
[Yu] Uh, hey!
♪ Looking up high ♪
[screams continue]
♪ Found a steel tower ♪
♪ Wondering how I would feel ♪
‐♪ If I fall down ♪
‐[screaming stops]
♪ Was it a dream ♪
♪ I saw deep red ♪
♪ Chasing all
that's far ahead ♪
♪ Always yearning ♪
♪ Don't know why ♪
♪ About the beauty
I really want ♪
♪ May seem to be awkward ♪
♪ To someone's eyes ♪
Kazuki Tomori. I'm a friend
of someone that you know.
Do you remember
a girl named Nao,
your little sister?
N...ao.
That's right, your sister!
Nao.
Ah! Thank goodness.
[Sala] Seems like some sort
of miracle just happened.
Yeah. Your song
was able to reach him.
You seem happy
from the bottom of your heart.
And that makes me
just as happy.
Yeah.
Thanks.
[Sala] Congratulations.
You moved one step forward.
Hey, I can't thank you enough.
I'm glad I was able to spend
such a fruitful day
with a brand‐new friend.
By the way, I managed
to snag a couple of tickets
to see your gig tomorrow night.
Yeah? Then even though I won't
be able to see you out there,
I'll be sure to
sing my heart out for you.
I'm guessing that the other
ticket's for that friend
you care about?
I'll sing for her, too, then.
Yeah, please do.
[Yu] So in the end,
Tomori, you were the one
that changed me.
[woman singing in Japanese]
[phone rings]
Hey, Otosaka speaking.
[Tomori] It's Tomori.
Do you want to hear what
happened with your big brother?
I already know.
I'm standing outside
the hospital right now.
We must have
just missed each other.
Yeah. I rushed over
after the nurses called
to tell me what happened.
Kazuki actually recognized me.
It's been a long time since
I've seen my brother like that.
I'm really glad.
Yes. You made
a wonderful decision.
I want you to know
I'm grateful.
[Tomori] Thank you very much.
[Yu] Yeah.
[Tomori] So, I'll see you
again tomorrow.
You haven't forgotten
about the gig, have you?
[Yu] Course not.
[soft music plays]
[Yu] So tomorrow
I'll hear her songs live.
Why does it feel
so nostalgic?