[alarm beeping]
[sighs]
Good morning. Huh?
[laughs] Good morning,
sleepy head!
Here, I made
some French toast for you.
[Yu thinking] It's red!
Since you won't be needing
lunches for school anymore,
I decided to put more effort
into your breakfast.
[Yu]
Put more effort, huh?
Looks like that's nothing more
than adding pizza sauce.
[Ayumi] Time to eat!
[Yu] The sugar
from the pizza sauce
mixed with the sugar
in the French toast!
Huh? What's wrong?
Does it taste weird?
Oh, no, it's fine.
Seems like I'm not feeling
too well.
Aww, did you catch a cold?
Maybe you should stay home
from school today.
It's not that bad.
I'm sorry that I'm
making you worry.
Are you sure
you're gonna be all right?
[Yu] I'm totally fine!
Thank you for the meal.
You really do look pale.
You should be taking
the day off today.
No, no, there's nothing wrong,
I promise.
[Yu] I need to find a place
to bury that pizza sauce.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
I got some amazing news.
Yusa Nishimori is transferring
into our school!
You mean the Yusarin?
No way.
This isn't a big art school
or anything.
If she's the real thing,
I'll be so happy.
As expected,
everyone is getting pumped.
There's going to be a riot
when she actually shows up.
Just thinking about it's
really got me on edge.
‐[door opens]
‐Quiet.
‐You there, sit down.
‐[boy] Seriously?
[teacher] Over here.
[Yusa giggles]
[teacher] Now, this transfer
student will be your classmate
starting today.
Introduce yourself.
I'm Yusa Kurobane,
known as Yusarin.
‐[cheering]
‐[teacher] Quiet!
I said be quiet!
You there, sit down.
And you there, stop dancing!
[Yu]
Even in a place like this,
she calls herself Yusarin?
So her real name is Kurobane?
How could you not even
know that much?
[inhales sharply]
Shhh!
I may not be able
to attend every day
because work can keep me
pretty busy,
but when I'm here,
I look forward
to enjoying high school life
with all of you.
It's a pleasure
to meet you all.
Yusarin! Yusarin!
Yusarin!
[all chanting "Yusarin!"]
‐[teacher] Sit down and shut up!
‐[Yu] Oh, brother.
Kurobane, you sit there.
That's your seat now.
It's nice to see you again.
Same. I'm sure
I'll trouble you a lot,
but I'll try to be
a good neighbor.
It's very nice
to see you, too.
‐[boy 1] What's with her?
‐[boy 2] She's so rude.
[girl] So not friendly.
[boy] Why did you
transfer here?
[girl] Oh, I preordered
your new single.
[girl 2] Me too.
It's such a great song.
‐[boy 1] I always watch
Movement Morning!
‐[boy 2] Me too, me too.
Will you please be my friend?
What's your email?
You bastard, what do you think
you're doing?
Don't try to cut us out.
[boy] I'm not doing
any such thing.
[Yusa] Now, now, both of you,
be nice to each other.
Ahh! Is she gonna do
what I think she is?
Huh? Do what?
[girl] Huh?
I cast a spell on you,
I cast a spell on you.
Now we can all make up
and be friends too!
[giggles]
There it is!
Yusarin's Magic Spell,
series number 13,
the spell for making up!
There,
now don't you two feel better?
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
All good, I was wrong.
‐[bell clangs]
‐[Yu] What is that so‐called
Magic Spell series?
Yusa was once
a regular cast member
of the hit morning information
show Movement Morning!,
or "Move‐Mo."
After the day's fortunes,
she'd send out various spells,
particularly towards the viewers
who had bad luck that day.
And just how many episodes
of this are there?
There are 64.
But two of them actually
overlap, so there are really‐‐
[Tomori] Big turnoff.
Hello. Will he be appearing
before us again?
Yes.
‐[giggles] Oh, thank you.
‐[boy] Oh, hey, watch it!
Kurobane, I'd like you
to come with us to
the student council room.
[students sigh]
[boy] Hey, Student Council
President, that's not cool.
Let's get going.
‐Right.
‐[Yu sighs]
Yusa, that Magic Spell
you did earlier,
series number 13,
the spell for making up,
it was fantastic!
Wow! I can't believe you know
so much about it.
Yes! I checked out the show
religiously for the entire time
you were a part of it.
Wow! Thank you very much.
[Yu]
You're such a fan boy.
Get over it, already.
I have a question.
What are we going
to do in here, exactly?
A comrade will arrive soon.
However, we should
probably get you
mentally prepared for him.
His unusual appearance
might shock you.
‐Huh?
‐[door crashes open]
Huh?!
[shoes sloshing]
‐[Yusa shivering]
‐Now, don't be afraid.
He's one of us.
He will never do harm to you.
The ability is telekinesis.
Um, can someone tell me
what just happened?
[Yu] Someone with
a special ability
is in this general area,
and the power he has
is telekinesis.
That guy found you
in exactly the same manner.
What? That's amazing!
I'm going to do my best.
All right!
[Yu] You know, you can get
possessed by spirits
and have pyrokinesis.
You're even more amazing.
Looks like another school.
I think it's Kannai Academy.
‐Yeah, bingo!
‐[Yu] Uh, what is?
This is the sports paper
from last week.
I've had my eye on this guy
for a while.
Wow! He pitched three perfect
games in a row.
"With sharp knuckleballs,
no doubt this super
high school level pitcher
will join the pro league."
[Tomori] The next day,
I went and watched them
practice.
Everyone should look at this.
Here we go.
Huh?
‐[umpire] Strike!
‐[Yu] Whoa.
That's one heck of a curveball.
He's like major league caliber.
It gets even better.
Watch some footage
where we get a closeup
of the pitcher's
throwing hand.
There. Take a look.
‐See something strange?
‐[Yu] Like what?
[Tomori] He's gripping it
like a fastball,
one that goes straight.
Knuckleballs are supposed
to move irregularly
by stopping the ball rotation
as much as possible.
The basic knuckleball is thrown
by putting your index
and middle fingers
against the ball like this.
How you grip a fastball
makes it spin
and it doesn't allow it
to wobble around like
a knuckleball does.
‐You sure know a lot.
‐I get it now.
He's using telekinesis
to move the ball around
after he's thrown it, isn't he?
‐Yes.
‐Wow!
That's amazing, right?
[Yu]
Does she get any of this?
It will be bad if we can't
get ahold of him
before the national
championship.
Let's head there right now.
[Yusa] Well, what about class?
[Tomori] It's all right.
No matter how we act,
as long as we're a part
of the student council,
there can be no demerits
towards our grades
or our school reports.
‐[coach] Left, right, left!
‐[Yusa] Is that so?
We're from the Hoshinoumi
Academy Student Council.
We're practicing right now.
What is it you guys want?
‐I'm sorry.
‐[boy] Yusa Nishimori?!
Could you just ignore her
for the moment and listen
to what I have to say, please?
[boy] What is it?
I'm not beating
around the bush here.
Do you use telekinesis
to control your knuckleballs
after you throw them?
Telekinesis?
As in supernatural abilities?
Are you insane?
Of course I don't.
Are you from some occult
research club instead of
the student council?
All right, wise guy,
listen closely.
That power of yours
is like a disease
that's only around
during your adolescence.
Even if you were aiming
to be a pro,
by the time you reach it,
it will be long gone.
Not only that, but if someone
notices you have powers,
you'll be captured.
Then you can kiss baseball
goodbye for good.
So from here on, don't use
that special ability of yours,
understand?
And who would capture me,
exactly?
Scientists who are experimenting
on people with abilities
just like you.
You expect me to believe
something that crazy?
‐[Yusa] Huh?
‐All right, fine.
Do me a big favor
and don't look away.
[Arifumi] What? Yaaa!
So, do you believe me now?
[Misa] You really are
a sore loser, aren't you?
I say that we roast
this chump.
[Yu] Hey!
‐What?
‐Oh, uh, my bad.
This isn't
the time to be showing off.
Huh! Ptooey!
Ohh! Yusarin's spit.
No, this is Misa's saliva.
‐I don't know how
I should react.
‐Turnoff!
Back to business.
So, how are we gonna
resolve this?
Hmm.
Hmm. I know.
How about a game of baseball?
‐Huh?
‐It'll be our baseball team
versus your baseball team.
And if we win, you have to do
whatever we say.
All right, then.
And if we win,
I don't see you ever again.
Deal. But still,
you'll never become
a professional baseball player.
I don't understand
what drives you to play.
What is it?
[Arifumi] I want to go to
the national championship,
that's all.
[Tomori, sighing] Understood.
Next Sunday at 3 p. m.
at our school courtyard.
How about it?
[Arifumi] I don't have
any problems with that.
What's wrong, Arifumi?
[Yu] So someone that can hit
that knuckleball exists
on our baseball team?
[Tomori] We'll be using
our abilities,
so it will be just fine.
And what kind of powers
does the team have?
They don't. They have several
people with potential
but no one's developed
a special ability yet.
Then how do we pull this off?
We'll be there to support them.
[Yu screams]
You mean we're all
a part of this?
We won't win otherwise.
Besides, if it's on
our school courtyard,
it won't turn into a riot.
That was the appropriate move.
I'm getting fired up now.
[Yu]
Don't you burn anything.
‐[Yusa giggles]
‐[umpire] Bow.
[all] Have a good game.
[Takato] Our opposing team
has girls in it, huh?
No way they can hit
your pitches.
What's the point
of this game, anyway?
It's all about the future,
Takato.
I see, all right.
Let's do this then.
If you lose, I'm smacking
all your asses, with this bat.
‐[Tomori] Win!
‐[team] Yeah!
[Yu] Smacking asses
with a bat?
What is she, an old woman?
Play ball!
Yes.
They must have
the worst batters on the planet
‐if they can't even hit
one of our balls.
‐Is that so?
Hey! I'm doing you a favor
being out there.
What kind of talk is that?
It's the truth.
Screw you, I'm outta here!
[Tomori] That won't do.
Please keep pitching.
Then think before you open
your big mouth!
Kurobane, please go ahead.
‐[Arifumi] Huh?
‐OK.
I cast a spell for thee,
I cast it, don't you see?
Now that you are nice and calm,
please smile for me!
‐[screams]
‐It's from Magic Spells
series number 9,
the spell for calming down!
Yep. Now everything's
gonna be A‐OK.
‐[sighs]
‐Knock it off!
‐[batter] Huh?
‐[umpire] Strike! Batter out.
That knuckleball's insane.
No way we're ever gonna hit it.
Just go ahead and smack me,
I don't care.
You know, it's pretty amazing
the catcher manages
to catch pitches like that.
[Yu] Guess that means that he's
super high school level, too.
There's no way we can win this.
[bat hits ball]
[Arifumi] We just need one run.
If the two of us can score
one run,
we can win, as long as
we protect that lead.
Here goes!
[Yu] Not good. So they went
after Yusa after all.
Misa, on the other hand,
has athletic reflexes.
‐Damn, why is Yusa so weak?
‐[Yu] I see.
She can make the right
decision, but she can't
physically keep up.
[umpire] Strike! Batter out.
[umpire] Out!
[ball hitting glove]
[bat hits ball]
[umpire] Ball four!
[Yu] Not looking good.
[umpire 2] Out!
[umpire 3] Safe!
[Yu] This is
a total crisis.
We should use abilities
as well.
‐[Yu] Specifically...?
‐[Tomori] You need to take over
the opponents' batters.
What I want you to do is make
the last two of them listless
so they barely swing their bats.
Throw outside
of the strike zone.
Just be careful to not
throw a wild pitch.
‐Yeah, got it.
‐All right now,
I'm counting on you.
[umpire] Play ball!
[Yu] Never thought
I'd use my powers
for something like this.
‐[umpire] Strike!
‐Huh? What the...?
What's the matter?
‐[ball hits glove]
‐[umpire] Strike two!
‐Hey, are you all right?
‐Yeah, totally fine.
It's two outs with the next guy.
Arifumi, if you want
to be that thorough
in winning this thing,
we have to go all out!
Catcher!
‐[umpire] Safe!
‐[cheers, shouting]
Takato.
[Yu] Wait,
what the hell happened?
‐I didn't think that far ahead.
‐Did he steal home base?
Damn, damn, damn!
Guess we ain't winnin' this one.
[ball hits glove]
[umpire] Strike! Batter out!
Just make sure that you hit
the ball when you bunt.
Then use your ability
to run past first base,
and don't forget to touch it.
Are you sure that they'll
see me make it there?
I'll record the evidence with
a super‐high‐speed camera.
Understood.
[umpire] Strike!
Strike two!
[Yu] If I screw up
the next one, I'm out.
[Arifumi] Here it comes,
four‐eyes.
[Yu groans]
‐Yes!
‐[whoosh!]
[Takato] Huh? Whoa!
[umpire] Uh...
He touched first base,
it's plain as day.
Come on now, it's safe.
Call safe!
Hmm... Safe!
[Takato] What the heck happened?
That was great.
We won't let it go to waste.
I need a pinch runner!
[Misa] Yusa's weak,
but I'll use my own game sense
to hit the ball.
All right!
That's the way.
It was awesome!
It's your turn to bat now,
so what are you going to do?
A sacrifice bunt,
and once it succeeds,
one base hit
will get us a walk‐off.
Huh? I can't hit like that
with my ability.
‐How about you go face things
head on once in a while?
‐[Yu] Huh?
Show me the fiend
that cheats on tests.
Please hit it!
‐Damn!
‐[player] First base!
‐They're just a bunch
of amateurs!
‐[umpire] Out!
[Yu] I have to face
this crap head on?
[Misa] Lead! Lead!
Strike!
‐Strike two!
‐Damn!
Foul ball!
I finally hit it.
‐[bat hits ball]
‐[umpire] Foul!
[umpire] Foul!
[Arifumi] Hmm.
His timing is inching closer.
I'll move it a bit more
on this one.
[Yu] Crap!
It's all over.
It's not over. Move it.
He fumbled!
[Yu] Huh? Oh!
[umpire] Safe!
We can do this.
I have the game sense!
Takato, home!
[screams]
Huh?
Safe! That’s the game!
[cheering, shouting]
[Misa] Did you see that?
I ruled!
[boy] That was amazing,
Yusarin!
‐So did we win?
‐Yes, by the skin of our teeth.
We won. That's awesome.
All right!
Wait, why am I getting so happy
about something like this?
[Tomori] We were victorious.
Please never use
that ability again, ever.
[Arifumi] I'm just
an ordinary pitcher.
But Takato, the catcher,
is different.
He's a catcher that really
deserves to be in the spotlight.
The two of us have played
together for a long time.
He knew that the baseball team
at our school was weak.
But still he chose
to pair up with me.
I just wanted
to take him to nationals,
even if it meant
using this power.
The nationals,
that big stage where even
pros would notice him.
So instead of personal gain,
you were using your ability
for your friendship.
‐That's right.
‐We won the game today because
we cheated with our abilities.
But you've been cheating while
pitching for quite a while.
But there are people
who will notice him out there,
even if you don't cheat,
and it doesn't matter
if it's in college or
in the business leagues.
You can keep watch over him
as his best friend.
Someday he'll shine out there
and you'll point to him and say,
"That is my closest friend."
‐I'm sure of it.
It'll be all right.
‐I know.
[Tomori] As a small experiment,
can you try taking over
his body?
Uh‐huh. What for?
Like I said,
it's an experiment.
You don't say that
to your test subject.
He's the test subject,
so don't worry.
[sighs] Whatever.
[sighs] Huh?
Huh? Whoa! What the...?
Thank you for indulging me.
No, it wasn't anything much.
Did you figure something out?
[Tomori] I'm not sure for now.
Just going to see how things go
for a while.
[Yu] I beg you, just this once,
can I have dinner
without pizza sauce?
‐[Yu] I'm back!
‐[Ayumi] A secret recipe
of the Otosaka house.
A cream stew full of broccoli!
[Yu] It's red!
But cream stew is supposed
to be white, isn't it?
That is what makes it
a secret family recipe.
[Yu] Just as I thought.
What do I believe in,
you ask?
I have to believe
in myself, of course.
[announcer]
The power to believe...
Oh! It's a new commercial
from Yusarin.
And it's How‐Low‐Hello's
new song.
That reminds me, did Yusarin
really transfer to your school,
Big Brother?
[Yu] Huh? Yeah.
That is just...
so incredibly amazing!
[shrieks]
[sighs]
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]