[beeping]
Since I was little,
I've had a question in my mind.
Why am I only myself
and not someone else?
I'm aware that
"I think, therefore I am"
are the words
of a great ancient philosopher,
but when I thought,
I thought about someone else,
that perhaps the other person
was myself, too.
[birds singing]
Think about others.
When I did that,
I turned into someone else...
[groaning]
...but for no more than
five seconds.
Furthermore, for the duration,
my body completely lost
consciousness
and just collapsed
wherever I stood.
I often found myself injured
in some way.
And I could only possess
someone that was within
my line of sight,
so I couldn't use it
for lewd things.
I mostly possessed people
who pissed me off,
picked a fight with a stranger,
and returned to myself.
That kind of retaliation
was all I could use this for.
‐[laughing]
‐[man] Oh, that's funny!
Huh?
[man] You bastard!
What the hell are you doing?
[invisible punches landing]
But finally, I came up
with a brilliant idea
that could take full advantage
of my special ability.
Hmm.
You have five minutes left.
I could possess
one smart person in class
after another,
memorize their answers,
and fill in my answers
after returning.
[student gasps]
[students murmuring]
[snickers]
Of course, I was planning
on attending a very
prestigious high school.
However,
unlike the normal test,
I didn't know who was
intelligent during
an entrance exam.
And so I snuck into
top‐rated cram schools,
one after another, pretending
to be one of the students
attending there.
Which students applied
to which schools
and which subjects
were they best at?
I researched
all of that thoroughly.
I found one student
after another
vying to enter
the same school I was
that I could possess
and take answers from.
And I was admitted
to an elite high school.
[man] Now a word from the
representative for new students.
‐Yu Otosaka, please come up.
‐Yes.
‐[boy] So that means he's
the very top of the class.
‐And he's good‐looking, too.
[clears throat, snickers]
[clears throat]
Today, for us new students,
you have organized a grand
ceremony to welcome us here,
and we are deeply grateful.
Wrapped in the warm rays
of the spring sunshine...
[girl] Hey, hey!
‐Huh?
‐He's really good‐looking,
isn't he?
Yeah. He might even be
your type.
My type, huh?
Well, I think you think he might
be your type, too!
‐Humph!
‐[titters]
On behalf of all of us,
thank you for the opportunity.
[applause]
[students murmuring]
Hmm.
[Yu] This again.
This is happening
more and more often.
Not only am I at the top
of the class academically,
I'm one of the more attractive.
It's impossible
to not be popular.
Sheesh! I'll just
hurry them all on home.
[Sugimoto] I'm sorry
for calling you
all the way out here.
Don't worry about it.
So, what did you want from me?
I, um... I'm fine starting
as just friends.
But can you maybe think
about dating me, please?!
The thing is,
in order to keep my grades up
at where they are now,
I have to shave time from sleep
to keep studying.
I don't have the luxury
of relationships.
So... I'm sorry.
Of course
that's a pack of lies.
I don't study at all, ever.
[Sugimoto] Oh, I see.
I understand.
I'm sorry for calling you out
like this so suddenly.
[Yu sighs]
[Yu] There's no way
I would ever choose
a plain, normal girl like you.
The one I'm after...
‐You mean you didn't watch
that TV special last night?
‐Huh‐uh.
...is the madonna
of this school, of course.
[girls giggle]
Yumi Shirayanagi.
I will make... you mine!
I know I'll definitely get
a chance.
It all lies in how I use
the five seconds,
which are the limits
of my ability.
‐[yawns]
‐[Yu] That's it!
‐So then I...
‐Huh?
[Yumi] Mitchon,
what's the matter?
‐[horn blaring]
‐[man] Did you see that?
She almost got run over.
[Yumi] Huh?
[man] It looks like
the airbag saved him.
[Yumi] I'm so glad.
[Yu sighs]
[Yu] That was close,
but it went according to plan.
Oh, Yumi!
‐[Mitchon] Are you all right?
‐Yeah, that was really
a close one.
Yumi, you were about to be
run over by a truck.
Otosaka from class one
ran out and saved you.
Really? Is that true?
Yeah. Are you hurt at all?
Ow!
Let's go to the nurse.
Can you walk?
Uh... yes.
[Yu] Well, guess I'll go home.
Please, wait a minute!
Um, you see, the two of us,
we're just about to walk over
to our favorite restaurant
to eat our favorite pancakes
together.
Would you like to come with us?
Sorry, I think I'm gonna pass.
It's better to keep this
among friends.
But you just put yourself
in danger in order
to save my life.
I'd like to properly repay that
and I'd like to talk with you
a little while longer.
Whoa, I have a phone call.
Who is it?
Huh? Then I'll go home
right away.
Mitchon, what's the matter?
My big brother suddenly
came back from Kyoto
and he apparently
ordered top‐end sushi
for the whole family.
So I'm leaving the rest
to you two. Bye!
[Yu] That was an obvious farce,
but a nice assist nonetheless,
Mitchon.
[waiter] Enjoy your meal.
[pop music in background]
Wait a sec, there's
a special way to eat this.
‐Uh...
‐Just copy me.
[Yumi] If you do this,
the syrup gets across
the entire thing.
Then stack them up,
cut them up,
and try a bite of it.
[gulp]
Mmm!
Amazing. Just by changing
how you eat it,
it gets this delicious?
I never realized.
It's delicious
every single time.
Uh... um...
The song they're playing
right now is "How‐Low‐Hello,"
isn't it?
[Yu] Huh? Hallow‐hello?
[Yumi] You look like you've
never heard of them.
I thought every boy our age
knew them really well.
So that's what's popular
nowadays?
[Yumi] Otosaka, can we walk
home together after school
or go out to eat like this
again sometime?
Hmm... Sure, I guess. Why not?
I'm so glad!
[Yu snickers]
[chuckles]
[Yu] I shouldn't do this
out loud.
I'll hurry on over.
[woman over loudspeaker]
Yu Otosaka from class 1‐1,
please report immediately
to the Student Council room.
‐I repeat...
‐What's this?
[woman] Yu Otosaka
from class 1‐1,
please report immediately
to the Student Council room.
[alerts chirping]
I'm Student Council
President Omura.
What is it you want with me?
I'm making someone wait, so I'm
hoping you can make this quick.
[Omura] That is completely
up to you.
This is an exact copy
of your answer sheet
to the aptitude test
you took the other day.
You managed a perfect score.
The same test has been placed
right there.
Right here and now, try to get
a perfect score again.
Huh? Why do I
have to take it again?
You've been accused of possibly
cheating on the exam.
If you score 90% or above,
you're innocent.
It not, you're guilty.
[Yu] This is ridiculous.
I'm leaving now.
Regarding this,
we have the support
of both the principal
and the vice‐principal.
If you leave now, you will be
expelled from school.
Expelled?!
[Omura] Now, please begin.
[Yu] All of the answers
are right there.
I'll just possess him
and find out what they are.
It's the only way.
He's making a fool of me!
Huh?
What in the world just happened?
[Yu] I don't know.
It seemed like you were
just tearing
whatever that was up.
We got enough.
[Yu screams]
I'm Tomori,
student council president.
Of another school, though.
So, I've been recording you
since you got here.
Please take a look at
the video I just recorded.
and take a note of the time.
You were not looking at Omura
the moment he ripped up
the answer sheet.
Yet you said he ripped it up.
Isn't that a bit strange?
I'll show you others.
You have a special ability
to possess other people.
Using that,
you cheat on every exam.
Isn't that right?
Th‐That's not true.
It's a sleeping disease.
I suddenly
get tremendously sleepy
and can't fight the urge
to nod off.
You really are troublesome.
I'll show you this, then.
Look.
A copy of a recent
medical exam.
[sighs] According to this,
you have no disease.
Now, please solve
the problems on the test.
[groans]
I can't deal with this!
Leave me alone!
There he goes.
She even foresaw that things
would end up this way.
Huh? Well then.
Everything from here on
is my job.
[gasping]
Start running! Right now!
[shrieks]
Damn it!
Are you injured?
No, I'm fine,
but what's wrong with him?
[scoffs]
[gasping]
Huh?
[boom!]
[muted shouting, alarm sounds]
[gasps, snarls]
[boom!]
What?! What the hell
is going on here?!
[panting]
[gasp]
[shrieks]
Uggh! [coughs]
What the hell?
What did you just do?
‐That was teleportation.
‐Teleportation?
Yes. Just like it sounds.
I instantly move
to another location.
Only I can't stop
where I want.
Thanks to my special ability,
I don't know how many times
I've been hospitalized.
[Yu thinking]
What a half‐assed ability.
So, anyway, what are you
planning on doing with me now?
[Tomori] We are having you
transferred over to our school.
Transfer?
[Tomori] In this world,
there are many people
who possess special powers.
‐You're not the only one.
‐What?
But those powers are somewhat
like an illness caught
during adolescence
and will disappear
in due time.
Until it goes away,
you will attend classes
at the Hoshinoumi Academy
with us.
I already have permission
from those that have
parental authority over you.
‐You mean all this is...?
‐Is real.
I gotta say, you seem
like you'd be popular
from just your good looks.
Did you really need to play
the genius by cheating
as much as possible?
That's the real question here,
isn't it?
But, thanks to that,
you were able to get close
to that female student
you were targeting.
[growls] Damn you!
[punches landing]
What the...? She disappeared?
‐That is her special ability.
‐[Yu] It can't be.
[Yu] How can you just become
invisible?
Actually, to me it looks like
you simply stood there
and let her punch you
in the face.
No way. I was the only one
that couldn't see her?
[Takajo] Right.
Her ability is to hide
from visual recognition
from one target.
Every other human
can see her as normal.
[Yu]
Another half‐assed ability.
By the way, you will be
expected to serve on
our student council as well.
‐[Yu] Huh?
‐Your ability is useful,
so I'd like for you
to cooperate with us.
To do what?
To threaten those that abuse
their powers for no good,
just like you have.
Because that is
the kind of existence we are.
[Yu, weakly] I'm home.
Oh, hi!
Welcome back home, Big Brother.
Wow! What's wrong
with your face?
Oh, well, I, um,
had an accident in gym class?
Oh, right, we got an amazing
phone call from our uncle
while you were gone.
He said that you and I
were immediately going
to be transferred
over to Hoshinoumi Academy's
middle school and high school
as scholarship students.
Is that really true,
Big Brother?
[Yu]
Are you serious?
[Yu] Yes, it's true.
Yay! This will be great
for the house budget!
And uncle is sending us
lots of tasty food
so that we can celebrate.
But this means that you
have to transfer schools.
You're gonna have to say
goodbye to all your friends.
Yeah, but we can use
smart phones
to video‐chat with one another,
so it's not going to be
all that big a deal.
[Yu drily] I see.
Tonight's dinner
is gonna be... ta‐da!
Omelet rice: your favorite dish,
Big Brother Yu.
[Yu] This again?
I've told her a million times,
it was only when I was little.
[Ayumi] Congratulations to us.
All right now, let's eat.
[giggles]
[Yu] So sweet!
Using this pizza sauce
as the secret ingredient
must have been fitting
for my tongue when I was
just a little child.
‐How is it? Is it tasty?
‐Yeah, it's tasty.
Wow, really?
It's the first time I've wanted
to eat Mom's omelet rice
in a while.
Our mom, huh?
Why would I even care
about someone like that?
Are you still upset?
Yeah, of course I am.
She selfishly divorced
and shoved custody
over to our uncle.
I don't understand much of it,
but I really wish you could be
more forgiving.
[Yu] We don't have parents
anymore.
Our only family is you and me.
I see.
But do you want to know
what I sometimes think?
That there is one more family
member out there somewhere.
You and I are the only siblings
we have.
Are you seeing someone
in your dreams?
Hmm, you're right.
But... it's a really
weird feeling,
as if it was actually true.
[Yu]
It's totally a dream.
Hey, we've got to be up
really early to move.
You should go get some sleep.
Oh, can't I have just a bit
more time, please?
Ayu, you really love stars,
don't you?
[Ayumi] You can see way off
into the distance, where people
will never reach, you know.
I just think that, well,
that it's an amazing thing.
[Yu] You know, if you
keep talking only about
the stars at school,
you'll end up isolated.
Really? Why is that?
In my experience,
a better strategy
is to try and liven up
the conversation,
by talking about movies and
TV shows instead of the stars.
Experience? Strategy?
It's OK if you don't get it.
Go to sleep soon.
[Ayumi] Roger that.
[guards snarl]
[Ayumi panting]
[giggles]
Whoa!
Wow!
This is an amazingly huge room!
Will you and I really be able
to use all this space alone,
Big Brother?
‐Uh, yeah.
‐[Ayumi] Thank you
for your hard work.
I may not be much,
but please allow me to help.
Hey, just let the moving company
guys do it, OK?
I thought that I could at least
be a little bit of help.
But I shouldn't?
[Yu] Don't take their jobs
away from them.
Oh, what an amazing way
to look at this.
I never would have thought
of that.
[Yumi] So, what was going on
with you the other day?
That's something I can't say.
Anyway, I'm going
to have to transfer over to
Hoshinoumi Academy immediately.
‐Huh?
‐I can't tell you why.
It's kind of complicated.
I'm sorry.
[Yu]
Until this ability goes away,
I can't be authorized to travel
to an area unsupervised.
If you could come out there
to see me once in a while,
that would be great.
Yeah, but that's just
so far away.
Maybe you can come here
every so often
and see me instead?
'Fraid not. I'm really sorry,
but I can't come
on my own anymore.
But why?
I'm not allowed
to tell you that.
I'm forced to not mention
anything about any of this
to others.
There's absolutely nothing
I can do about it.
I'm very grateful
for what you've done.
That feeling
will never leave me.
However, the fact is that you
and I aren't dating yet,
so for me to chase you
in a one‐sided way like that
would make me feel
like some kind of stalker.
I really do feel bad about that.
But I can't come see you
on my own.
[Yumi] I understand.
From now on, let us walk
our own separate ways.
What? But that means...?
I will never forget the feeling
I have towards you.
You saved my life that day,
and I will forever be grateful.
And that is all.
This can't...
Thank you very much
for saving me like you did.
I really do appreciate it.
But this is where I bid you
a fond farewell.
Best of luck to you.
[Yu] I got dumped!?
Me?
[doorbells jangle,
door closes]
[girl] Hello?
‐Excuse me, I let myself in.
‐[Yu screams]
Why are you suddenly here?
It's tough
with just two of you.
We came here to help out.
[Ayumi] Oh, hi.
Are all of you from
the same high school
as my big brother?
Yes. We're in
the student council.
My name is Takajo
and this is Tomori.
Since it's after school now,
we thought we should stop by
and see if we could help.
You shouldn't have bothered.
[Tomori] Can we help you out,
please?
Of course,
we'd love to have your help.
Hmm.
[Yu]
Yeah, petty cunning.
So let's split up
and get things done.
Right!
Thank you so much.
[Yu] Huh? This must be
that tasty food
our uncle sent
to congratulate us
that Ayumi was talking about.
Whaaa...?
It's all instant ramen?!
I'll pretend I never saw this.
Ayumi, can I show you
a magic trick?
[Ayumi] Oh. Yeah, Tomori.
I'd love to see one.
Now, stay right there.
I'll be back in just a second.
OK. What?
[nervous breathing]
Huh?
[shrieks]
That was amazing!
Even more amazing than
the people who are on TV.
Did you enjoy that?
[Yu]
Don't use her ability
to mess around.
You wowed her
out of her senses.
[Yu] If you're going to play,
you have to go home.
All right, fine.
Your big brother is scary.
Well, at least I appreciate
you helping us.
I guess it's time for us
to excuse ourselves.
You're going home?
But I'm going to make dinner
and I'd love it
if you two would stay.
We don't have enough dishes.
‐Right, if he says so.
‐Oh!
[Tomori] It's all right,
'cause we'll meet again.
[Ayumi] Hmm.
[Ayumi giggles]
[woman singing in background]
[Ayumi] Oh! "How‐Low‐Hello."
So it is a fad after all.
Ah, that's right!
Yusa Nishimori, Yusarin.
‐I think she's so cute.
‐[Yu sighs]
[Yu] That something
like this sells is a sign
of the apocalypse.
You know what, Big Brother?
My new school is literally
right next to yours,
so I think that we
should walk together.
People might think I have
a thing for my sister.
[Ayumi] A thing for me?
You brought me a present?
What? No.
Hoshinoumi, sea of stars.
What an absolutely wonderful
name for a school.
Yeah. It's a name that sounds
like it was created
with only you in mind. Hmm?
[bells chiming, Ayumi gasping]
[Yu] Hey.
[Yu] That night,
I had a dream.
I'm sure it was because
of Ayumi's far‐fetched
announcement.
But... who was that?
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]