[sighs]
I'm so sorry.
I don't think I'll be able
to make breakfast for you.
You're not doing anything
with a high fever.
You keep resting.
I'll call the school for you.
And I don't want you
making dinner either.
If you say so.
‐[teacher] Oikawa.
‐[Oikawa] Here.
Otosaka.
Oh, right. Otosaka is absent
today with a cold.
‐[teacher] Kato.
‐[Kato] Here.
‐[teacher] Kijima.
‐[Kijima] Here.
‐[teacher] Kiyama.
‐[Kiyama] Here.
‐[teacher] Konishi.
‐[Konishi] Here.
‐[teacher] Komatsu.
‐[Komatsu] Here.
‐[teacher] Komiyama.
‐[Komiyama] Here.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]
[footsteps sloshing]
‐[whoosh!]
‐[students gasp]
The ability is collapse.
[thud!]
[Yu groans]
Collapse?
Any idea what that could be?
No. My guess is, they can
destroy anything they target
at will.
Still a guess.
[Yu thinking] The fact that
it's not destruction
is kind of scary.
‐[Tomori] Where is this guy?
‐[Takajo] Let's see.
What? No way.
[Takajo] This is
our condo complex.
Cool. Then we don't have to
worry about them.
[Tomori] Is that so?
This person is sitting
in their condo right now.
‐Don't you think
that's a little strange?
‐[Yu] Why is that?
Parents can't be wielders
of special abilities,
'cause it only happens
during adolescence.
‐Yeah, that's right.
‐So then that means...
They caught a cold and are
absent from school or something.
[Yu] Impossible!
Hey, I saw that.
What's with the sudden anxiety?
I'm sure that it's nothing.
Why don't you let me
be the judge of that?
My little sister is...
sick at home.
‐[girls] Hmm.
‐[Yu gasps]
This might be proof that
if one sibling has an ability,
the other will, too.
Interesting.
Well, we're no scientists,
but still,
I say we visit Ayumi
and see if she's really
turned into a wielder
of a special ability
while we're at it.
Wait. Won't it seem strange
if all of you drop by at once?
[Tomori] Oh, right.
Then I guess I'll just
go by myself.
[Yu] No way.
Ayumi is a fan of Yusa.
If I bring her along,
I'm sure Ayumi would be happy.
Is something wrong?
But the fan boy
might get in my way.
I want it to be
just Tomori and Yusa.
Maybe I should take over
his body and make him jump
from the window.
Cool. So that's how
a giraffe sleeps, huh?
Yes, indeed. They sleep by
wrapping their necks around
in a coil
Wait, there's a giraffe here?
Where? I don't see it anywhere.
Hyah!
[screams]
‐[shrieking]
‐[Tomori] Whew!
I thought it was
kind of senseless for him
to come with us.
‐[Yu] Way to go, Tomori!
‐Is he OK?
He's got a full‐body
protector suit on.
He's fine as long as he didn't
fall head‐first.
Someone just fell out
of a window.
Could you send an ambulance,
please?
Now, once school lets out
for the day,
the three of us
will go visit Ayumi.
I'd like to buy a get‐well gift,
so we'll stop
at a convenience store.
Oh, me too. I want to buy
something for her as well,
please.
I was just thinking
I might want to buy
a few porridge packs
on my way home.
[Tomori] So, what do you think,
Yusa,
shall we eat the same thing
as Ayumi and you
‐and have porridge for dinner?
‐Sounds good to me.
You guys can eat
whatever you want once you
get to your own homes.
[Tomori] I suppose if we were
in the way, we could...
‐I think it would be a lot
better if we ate together.
‐Why do you say that?
Because...
I'm living away
from my parents, too,
so I'm all alone,
even if I go home.
[Tomori] I'm used
to being alone.
But Kurobane just moved out
recently.
Maybe what she says is true.
[Yu] No. Yusa
isn't the only one.
[Tomori] I swore that I wouldn't
trust anyone ever again.
I snuck out of that school.
[Yu] Her father sold her off
to scientists.
She couldn't trust after that.
She's still alone, too.
The fact that I have a sister
makes me fortunate.
All right, fine.
We can all eat porridge
for dinner together.
‐[beep]
‐[cashier] Your total
is 1,360 yen.
[Yu] That’s way more
than I've got!
Hey, don't worry.
I'll pay for this.
And these, too.
Is that... stewed enoki?
Yeah! Stewed enoki mushrooms
are the best!
They'll make the perfect topping
for our porridge tonight.
We don't all have
strange tastes like you.
Well, I really don't care as
long as you're paying for it.
I'm glad you see it that way.
Excuse me, that big can
of cookies back there...
can I have that?
I've never seen anyone
buy that before!
‐That one is 2,500 yen.
‐That's way too pricey!
[Yu] And what the heck
is with that fancy bag?
I've never seen anyone
buy that, either.
Then again, I didn't even know
it was an option.
[clerk] Thank you so much!
It's this one.
My sister is
a pretty huge fan of yours.
Awesome! That makes me
look forward to meeting her
even more.
However, don't forget
she's in bed with a fever.
We can't let her get
too excited.
At the very least,
she'll get a nosebleed.
‐Huh?
‐I want things to go gradually.
"Oh, wow, could that be
Yusarin?"
So don't go full‐on idol
from the start.
Don't worry. I have a disguise
for exactly this kind
of situation.
[Yu] Perfect.
Now, wait out here
for a few moments.
[lock thrown]
Hmm? Guests?
I wonder who.
Huh? Look, everyone,
my big brother is finally home.
Oh! Sorry for
the intrusion, sir.
I'm Nomura,
the class representative.
We came here in order to visit
Ayucchi while she's sick.
[boy] I'm Oikawa.
I'm very lucky to have
your sister as a friend.
It is a pleasure to meet
a member of her family.
Can your brown‐nosing
be more obvious?
You already got rejected.
Ayucchi will hate you even more
if you do that.
[Yu] So this is the guy
that asked Ayumi out
and got dumped?
Hmm?
[Nomura] Sorry to barge in
with so many people.
Come on now,
it's time to go home.
I'm sorry for being
so rowdy just then, sir.
‐Ayucchi, get better soon, OK?
‐[Oikawa laughs feebly]
Hey, Ayumi. Sorry to barge in.
How you feeling today?
Wait, I didn't call for you
just yet.
Oh, I thought it was
just a personnel swap.
Ahh! Hi, Tomori.
I'm so glad you're here!
It's good to see you again, too.
Oh, I see. The two of you
must be dating now.
‐[both] No way.
‐Aww! You look good together.
Anyway... we have
one more guest.
[Yusa] Nice to meet you.
It's Yu... sa... rin.
I knew this would happen!
[Yusa] She saw through me
instantly.
I got this. Make sure to breathe
from your mouth a little bit.
[Ayumi breathing]
All right,
you're in the clear.
Oh! You're right.
That's such an amazing trick.
‐[Ayumi sighs]
‐I'm so glad.
It's Yu... sa... rin!
[Tomori] I got it.
Should I cast my magic charm
that stops nosebleeds?
No, I think it will
do the exact opposite
of what you intend.
[Ayumi sighs]
My, what a surprise.
Yusarin actually here
in my home.
Have you finally calmed down?
Oh, good.
That's much better.
Oh, here are some cookies
as a get‐well gift.
I really hope you enjoy them.
[Ayumi] No way! I made Yusarin
worry about me!
[Yu] Try not to think of that
right now, OK?
‐She's just one of
my classmates, that's all.
‐Yep, yep, yep.
[Ayumi sighing]
[Yu] Her speech patterns are
starting to catch on already.
Now, the get‐well gift
from me. Ta‐da!
Oh! Stewed enoki. Thank you.
Do you have an appetite
right now?
‐We bought you
some pouched porridge.
‐What about you?
‐We're eating porridge too.
‐Yay! It's a porridge party!
[all] Time to eat!
[Ayumi and Yusa]
It's so super‐duper delicious.
I know, isn't it?
[Ayumi and Yusa]
Thank you for the meal.
‐That was oddly satisfying.
‐[phone rings]
Excuse me.
Hi, Yusa speaking.
Of course.
Oh, yes, I understand.
I'll be seeing you soon.
I'm really sorry, but I have to
go to work right now.
Whaaat?!
You're talking
to a show biz celebrity.
Stop complaining.
Oh! You know,
you’re absolutely right.
Go out there and rock
their socks off, OK?
Good night, and thank you
for the delicious food.
‐Ayumi, please get better soon.
‐You know it.
Thank you for visiting me,
Yusarin.
You're welcome back any time,
so don't be shy.
[Tomori] So, I guess
we'll clean up now.
You're not going to wash them?
There’s not that many.
I'll do it later.
‐Aaah!
‐Don't be such a slob!
We're cleaning 'em.
I'll handle scrubbing,
and you'll dry them.
O...K.
Huh. I think you two are dating
and keeping it a secret
from me.
[both] Not happening.
You're so compatible.
You even talk at the same time.
‐[both] No, we don't.
‐See what I mean?
Admit it, you'd make
a totally great couple.
I'd never be a good match
for someone as intelligent
as your brother.
His looks alone put him
way out of my league. Ha‐ha.
[sighs] I think you're
such a good match
that you're even
too good for him, Tomori.
[Yu] Don't be fooled, Ayumi.
She might as well be
calling me dumb and ugly.
Hey, why don't you watch
some TV?
[sighs]
Whatever.
[Yusarin singing]
Wow! That was fast.
Yusarin must be supersonic.
[Yu] That's prerecorded.
Oh, yeah, I see. [giggles]
[Yu] Here, take this.
You should turn in
for today.
I'll tuck you in, OK?
Good thing you have
a great big brother.
‐[Yu gulps]
‐[Ayumi] Yeah, but...
[Ayumi] I'm a little scared
of going to sleep.
Huh? What's the matter?
I had a scary dream
this afternoon.
Well, it's pretty common
to have nightmares and stuff
when you're running
a high fever.
There's nothing
to be uneasy about.
By the way, what kind of dream
were you having?
Don't ask her that.
It will just remind her of it.
Yes, you're right.
Anyway, I'll get
out of your hair.
Get well soon, kiddo.
Thanks for coming.
I hope to see you again soon.
I'm going to go see her off.
Back in a bit.
Whoo‐hoo‐hoo!
[both] It's nothing like that.
[Tomori] Please ask her
what the nightmare was about.
It might be a clue
to figuring out what
the collapse ability is.
Hold on. We still don't have
proof that Ayumi is the one
with the special ability.
It can be someone else that
lives in this condo complex.
It's true that we don't
have proof,
but the possibility is still
incredibly high.
And collapse...
I can't help but feel
that it will be dangerous.
[Yu] That's the same terror
I felt initially.
So, get it out of her soon.
This is for Ayumi's sake
as well.
Yeah, all right.
[Tomori] Even if her fever
goes down,
make her stay home tomorrow
just in case.
As it stands, we don't have
enough information.
Yeah.
[door opens]
‐[Yu] I'm back.
‐Welcome back, lover boy.
Hey, Ayumi, that bad dream.
You think you can tell me
what it was about?
[Ayumi] Hmm... Sorry. I don't
remember it all that well.
‐Even a vague idea?
‐Hmm...
Something breaks.
What does?
[Ayumi] I think the ground?
‐What kind of ground was it?
‐Uh...
It's really hard to remember
that much detail.
It was like there were
cracks in the ground
and it was splitting up.
Oh, why are you asking
about this anyway?
Uh...
Wouldn't it be scary
if it came true?
Come on,
nightmares don't come true.
That's just spiritual
mumbo‐jumbo.
[Yu] The world is full of
spiritual things, though.
[Takajo]
The ground splitting up?
Is that some kind of hint?
Maybe that ability
is something so horrible
that it will also rope in
the person using it.
[groans] We still don't have
enough information.
[Yusa] So, what should we do?
For now we can do surveillance.
We'll use the cameras set up
around the middle school
to watch the ability;
that will allow us to get
the information we need.
Also, we should let
the teachers know to keep
their eyes on Ayumi.
The middle school has
lots of people, so it will be
dangerous if something happens.
It's safer for her
at the condo.
I'd like to be more prepared,
so make sure she stays home
from school again tomorrow.
[Yu] All right, I can do that.
Should I go cast a magic spell
that cures her cold?
There it is! Yusarin's
Magic Spell series, 21.
If you have a cold,
it's the only cure for you!
‐[Tomori] Shut up!
‐[Yu] She'll probably get
a nosebleed again,
so I'd like you to pass
this time.
OK. Then I'll just visit
once she's feeling better.
[Yu] Yeah. That helps a lot.
[Yu] 36.5°.
Your fever's gone down.
I fought off the illness,
Commander.
I'm ready to return
to active duty and doing
what I do best.
So you didn't have
a weird dream?
‐No.
‐Look, you're still recovering.
I think you should stay home
one more day.
Aww! But I'm losing my mind
staying in bed all day long.
I wanna go back to school!
[Yu] There's still a chance
that your cold will relapse.
Trust me, it's for the best.
So you just suck it up
and get back in bed, all right?
‐No excuses.
‐Aww!
I'll contact your school.
[whining]
I may be a little girl,
but I'm not some pushover
you can keep locked up all day.
The grudge of the pizza sauce
will be avenged!
[Takajo humming]
[Yu] Are your injuries
healed already?
I'm assuming you mean
the injuries
from when I was pushed through
the window two days ago?
‐Uh, yeah.
‐I've gotten used to
Tomori‐induced injuries,
so I can bounce back
from them fairly quickly.
Though, when I first met her,
it was an instant trip
to the hospital.
[Yu] If I was in
your shoes, I'd never be able
to deal with it all.
It really makes me unsure
whether or not Tomori
should be leader.
You know, she's a lot more
calculating than you
give her credit for.
[vibrating]
Darn it.
She’s calling us already?
Let's hurry up and eat.
Took you long enough.
[Takajo] Both of us
were eating pasta,
so we couldn't wolf it down,
sorry about that.
[Tomori] Why the hell were you
twirling pasta around your fork
at a time like this?
What's up?
Did something happen?
Ayumi is at school right now.
Huh? No, I contacted her school
and made her stay home,
just like you told me to.
What was her condition?
Well, her fever was gone,
but I was worried
about her relapsing,
so I told her to stay home
one more day.
Her temperature's normal.
She decided to go
and attend school
from the third period onward.
I have a bad feeling.
We need to go check
on Ayumi right away.
[guard] Huh?
Uh, nice seein' ya, miss.
[Oikawa] Um, Otosaka?
I recently found a sweet shop
that serves really good
red bean soup.
I'd like to treat you
to some, OK?
I'm sorry,
but I just got better,
so I have to pass, Oikawa.
[gasp] Wait. Hold on a second!
If right after getting better
is bad, how about we go
on the weekend?
[Nomura] Thud!
You really don't get it, do you?
You've already been denied once,
so just give up.
Move it! If you don't get out
of my way, I'll make you!
Oh, put a sock in it.
Don’t worry.
I can handle this guy.
You go on ahead.
I really appreciate it, Nomura.
[Oikawa] Wait. Otosaka!
Hold on!
[Nomura] Just give it up!
[Yu] Why are we doing this
again?
It's a shortcut.
Huh?
Konishi?
It's all because you showed up.
Huh? What is?
[Konishi] With Oikawa...
What are you talking about?
I used to eat lunch with him
all alone, every single day.
We were supposedly dating.
But ever since you showed up,
Oikawa...
Oikawa, it's like he's
completely forgotten about me!
He just looks at you
all the time!
[shrieks, gasps]
[Ayumi gasps]
Wait, Konishi, please
listen to me!
It's just a misunderstanding.
Put that box cutter away, OK?
It's all your fault.
[blade clicking]
No, that's not true!
That why I'll make you
feel pain for a change!
Someone, please.
Help me! Help me!
‐[Nomura snickers]
‐[Ayumi] Help me!
[whoosh!]
[screams]
[Tomori] This is...
the collapse.
‐[gasping]
‐[bell rings]
[Medoki] We didn't
make it in time.
‐I'm going in!
‐You can't, it's too dangerous!
Ayumi... Ayumi!
Don't go!
You'll get trapped inside.
Ayumi!
[bricks rattling]
‐[screams]
‐Hey, what are you doing?
Get away from there,
it's dangerous!
Ayumi! Ayumi!
[column rumbling]
Huh?
[theme song plays]
[thunder rumbles]