Sky Raker:
SO. YOU MUST BE
SILVER CROW.
IT’S SO NICE
TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS SKY RAKER.
I’M HAPPY YOU
CAME OUT HERE TO SEE ME.
( gasps )
YEAH, WELL,
OKAY, MASTER.
I GUESS I’M, UH,
GONNA GET GOIN’ THEN.
HUH?
HOLD ON A SEC.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
LISTEN UP, CROW.
I DON’T KNOW WHAT’S GOIN’ ON
WITH YOUR PUNK ASS, BUT JUST
BECAUSE YOU LOST YOUR WINGS
DOESN’T MEAN YOU SHOULD
GIVE UP ON THEM SO EASILY.
IF YOU DID THAT, THEN FOR ALL
OF US DUDES WHO’VE BEEN WATCHING
YOU FLY AROUND THIS WHOLE TIME,
IT’D BE...
DAMN IT!
I DON’T KNOW HOW TO PUT IT,
SO JUST DO SOMETHING,
YA BIG PANTY WASTE!
B-BUT HOW?
Sky Raker:
MR. CROW.
THIS IS WHERE
ASH THINKS I MAY
BE OF SOME USE.
PERHAPS THERE’S A WAY
I CAN HELP GET
YOUR WINGS BACK.
WHAT? YOU GUYS ARE
WILLING TO HELP ME?
BUT...AREN’T YOU WITH
THE GREEN LEGION?
DON’T GET THE
WRONG IDEA.
I’M NOT DOING THIS
FOR YOU.
SEE, IT’S ALL
PART OF A PLAN.
A SECRET MISSION TO
BOOST MY POPULARITY.
THEN WE’LL GET YA OVER ON OUR
SIDE AND HAVE YOUR SHINY ASS
TURN ON THE BLACK LEGION.
MEGA FUCK YEAH,
BABY! ( laughs )
ASH, YOU’RE BEING
CRUDE AGAIN.
OH!
SO SORRY, MASTER!
DESPITE ASH’S FOUL MOUTH,
LOOKS, AND GENERAL LACK
OF INTELLIGENCE,
THERE ARE MANY
GOOD PARTS AS WELL.
SO THAT’S...
SKY RAKER...
ONCE KNOWN AS THE ONLY BURST
LINKER IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD
WHO EVER CAME CLOSE TO FLYING.
UM...SO,
MISS RAKER.?
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN HELP ME
GET MY WINGS BACK?
I’M AFRAID
THE ANSWER IS NO.
( gasps )
WHENEVER YOU LOSE
SOMETHING FROM YOUR DUEL
AVATAR, IT’S NEVER RANDOM.
THERE’S ALWAYS SOME SORT OF
REASON BEHIND IT.
AND WHATEVER THAT REASON IS,
I CAN’T HELP MAKE IT GO AWAY.
SO, THEY’RE GONE FOR GOOD?
YES. NO MATTER WHAT WE DO
IN THIS GARDEN, YOUR WINGS
WILL NEVER COME BACK.
BUT...THAT DOESN’T MEAN
YOU WON’T FLY AGAIN.
( gasps )
♪
I’VE BEEN RATHER
INTERESTED IN YOU FOR
QUITE SOME TIME NOW.
SEVEN YEARS AFTER
THE INCEPTION OF
ACCELERATED WORLD,
WE FINALLY HAVE
AN AVATAR WITH
AVIATION ABILITIES.
IT MAKES ME WONDER
WHAT SORT OF SOUL YOU HAVE.
THE PSYCHOLOGICAL SCARS
YOU CARRY.
THOSE TRAITS HAVE CREATED
A POWER THAT DEFIES GRAVITY.
IT’S NOTHING SPECIAL.
I WAS JUST BULLIED
A WHOLE LOT IN REAL LIFE.
AND I DON’T KNOW IF I
WOULD GO SO FAR AS TO CALL
THEM "PSYCHOLOGICAL SCARS."
DON’T FORGET, THE SCARS THAT
DEFINE THE LOOK OF YOUR AVATAR
AREN’T SOLELY ABOUT HOW MUCH
ANGER OR HATRED YOU HAVE.
HUH?
A SCAR IS A SIGN THAT
SOMETHING’S MISSING.
SOMETHING IMPORTANT TO YOU
HAS BEEN REMOVED, LEAVING
A HOLE IN YOUR HEART.
HAVING THAT EMPTY HOLE
CAN LEAD YOU TO ANGER,
HATRED, OR DESPAIR.
OR IT CAN DO THE OPPOSITE
AND PUSH YOU TO REACH HIGHER.
THE DIRECTION YOU CHOOSE
IS REFLECTED IN THE
STATE OF YOUR AVATAR.
IN OTHER WORDS, THOSE
PSYCHOLOGICAL SCARS ARE
YOUR HOPES TURNED INSIDE OUT.
SILVER CROW, YOUR WISH
FOR THE SKY WAS STRONGER
THAN ANYONE ELSE’S.
AND IT WAS THE STRENGTH OF THAT
WISH THAT GAVE YOU YOUR AVIATION
ABILITY AND YOUR WINGS.
IT WASN’T YOUR WINGS
THAT GAVE YOU FLIGHT.
IT’S THE OPPOSITE.
IT’S BECAUSE YOU ALREADY
HAD THE CAPACITY TO FLY
THAT YOU HAD WINGS.
REALLY?
SO, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT I DIDN’T ACTUALLY
NEED MY WINGS, THAT
THEY WERE JUST FOR SHOW?
IN A LITERAL
INTERPRETATION, YES.
THERE’S NO WAY!
LOOK, EVEN IF I DID
TRULY WANNA FLY, BRAIN BURST
IS WHAT SENSED THAT IN ME.
THAT’S WHAT GAVE ME
MY WINGS AND AVIATION ABILITY.
I HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
SO, BASICALLY,
WHAT YOU’RE SAYING...
IS THAT WHEN IT COMES TO
THE ACCELERATED WORLD,
WILL POWER MEANS NOTHING.
( gasps )
TAKE A GOOD LOOK AT
MY WHEELCHAIR.
IT HAS NO CONTROLS
AND NO MOTOR ATTACHED.
HOWEVER...
NO WAY.
ONE OF THE FUNDAMENTAL ASPECTS
OF BRAIN BURST IS TO MIMIC
REALITY AS CLOSELY AS IT CAN.
AND YET...
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
WHAT’S ACTUALLY
POWERING YOUR CHAIR?
THE ONLY THING THAT’S
MAKING MY CHAIR MOVE
IS WILL POWER.
YOU MEAN LIKE, SOME SORT
OF PSYCHOKINETIC ABILITY?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
THE TRUTH IS, EVERY PLAYER
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD HAS
THE CAPACITY TO DO THIS AS WELL.
( gasps )
( giggles )
YOU DON’T BELIEVE ME?
YOU MIGHT UNDERSTAND BETTER IF
YOU THINK OF IT AS VISUALIZATION
POWER INSTEAD OF WILL POWER.
VISUALIZATION?
FIRST, I FULLY VISUALIZE
AN IMAGE OF MY TWO
WHEELS SET IN MOTION.
AND THROUGH THE INCARNATION
OF THIS IMAGE, I CAN
CONTROL MY WHEELCHAIR.
( gasps )
I’M SURE THAT
WHEN YOU’RE FLYING,
YOU’RE SUBCONSCIOUSLY USING THE
SAME METHOD TO POWER YOUR WINGS.
OUR POWER TO VISUALIZE...
THAT IS THE TRUE POWER
HIDDEN WITHIN ALL BURST LINKERS.
AND FOR THE PLAYERS WHO HAVE
MANAGED TO MASTER THIS SKILL
AND USE THIS POWER
TO CONTROL THINGS...
THEY HAVE A NAME FOR IT.
THE INCARNATE SYSTEM.
A POWER THAT TAPS INTO
YOUR HEART’S DEEPEST HOPES.
IN OTHER WORDS, YOUR WILL.
THE INCARNATE...
SYSTEM?
SO, ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME
THAT IF I CAN SOMEHOW LEARN TO
USE THIS INCARNATE SYSTEM...
THEN I’LL BE
ABLE TO FLY AGAIN?
LET ME SHOW
YOU SOMETHING.
( gasps )
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR LEGS?
WERE THEY STOLEN FROM YOU,
LIKE MY WINGS?
NOT EXACTLY.
I WANTED TO HAVE THEM
CUT OFF. SO I GOT SOMEONE
TO DO IT FOR ME.
IT WAS AN ACT OF
ARROGANCE, EGOTISM,
AND INSANITY.
BUT AT THE
TIME, THAT’S WHAT I DID.
TO FORCE MY WILL OF WANTING
TO FLY TO BE AS STRONG AS
IT POSSIBLY COULD.
( gasps)
DID IT WORK?
COULD YOU FLY?
NO.
INCARNATION DID HELP INCREASE
MY JUMPING ABILITY.
BUT I’M AFRAID I NEVER
DID QUITE MAKE IT TO FLYING.
WHAT DO YOU
THINK, MR. CROW?
NOW THAT YOU’VE SEEN
THESE FOOLISH SCARS,
DO YOU STILL WISH TO
LEARN HOW TO FLY USING
THE INCARNATE SYSTEM?
LOOK...I CAN’T QUIT.
THERE’S STILL A TON
OF THINGS THAT I HAVE TO DO.
SO PLEASE, TEACH ME
HOW TO USE INCARNATION!
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
IT TAKES A VERY LONG TIME.
THERE’S EVEN THE POSSIBILITY
THAT IT WILL TAKE YOU
PAST THE POINT OF NO RETURN
FOR A BURST LINKER.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT WHATEVER IT TAKES,
I’LL DO IT.
VERY WELL, THEN.
BUT FOR NOW, WE REST.
THAT’S ENOUGH
FOR TODAY.
HERE YOU ARE.
UM...
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
UH, I DON’T REALLY
HAVE A MOUTH...
AAH!
UH, NEVER MIND.
SORRY.
( slurping )
IT’S AMAZING!
TAKE YOUR TIME
AND FULLY SAVOR
THE TASTE.
MAKE IT A MEMORY
THAT WILL TRULY LAST.
UM, CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING?
GO AHEAD.
IT’S ABOUT MR. ASH.
HAS HE BEEN TRAINED
ON INCARNATION?
NOT PROPERLY.
I’VE GIVEN MY PROTEGE A FEW
TIPS, BUT THAT’S ABOUT IT.
ASH IS TRYING HARD, THOUGH.
IF YOU’RE HIS GUARDIAN,
DOES THAT MEAN YOU’RE IN
THE GREEN LEGION TOO?
NO.
I’VE ONLY EVER BEEN
IN ONE LEGION.
AND I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF CHANGING THAT.
I SUPPOSE YOU HAVE
THE RIGHT TO KNOW
WHICH ONE IT IS.
LET ME TELL YOU
A LITTLE BEDTIME STORY.
ABOUT A FOOLISH BURST LINKER
WHO REACHED FOR THE SKY.
AND WHAT HAPPENED TO HER
ONE AND ONLY FRIEND.
ALL RIGHT, WE’RE
ABOUT TO START YOUR
INCARNATION TRAINING.
I’M READY.
AND I PROMISE
TO DO MY BEST.
THE ESSENCE OF
INCARNATION CAN BE
DISTILLED INTO ONE WORD.
ONCE YOU UNDERSTAND
IT, YOU CAN USE IT
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
JUST ONE WORD?
THAT’S RIGHT.
WELL, WILL YOU TELL
ME WHAT THAT WORD IS?
OF COURSE.
HOWEVER...
( stammering )
I’D PREFER TO TELL YOU
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET.
( yelling )
KNOWING MISS RAKER,
I SHOULD HAVE GUESSED
IT WASN’T GOING TO BE EASY.
"NEXT TIME WE MEET"?
SO I GOTTA CLIMB
TO THE TOP OF THIS THING?
THAT’S ASKING A LOT.
BUT I’LL DO IT.
ALL RIGHT. I’VE PLAYED
A FEW CLIMBING GAMES BEFORE.
JUST WATCH!
I’VE MANAGED TO COME
PRETTY FAR.
( grunting )
IT’S OKAY.
MY AVATAR’S BODY
IS SLIM AND SMOOTH,
AND HAS VERY LITTLE
AIR RESISTANCE.
SO I SHOULDN’T BE
BLOWN OFF THAT EASILY.
GREAT, I’M NEARLY THERE.
IF I CAN CLIMB ALL THE WAY TO
THE TOP ON MY FIRST DAY,
MISS RAKER IS GONNA BE
TOTALLY IMPRESS--
WHAT? A TRANSITION?
DAMN IT!
( gasping )
THE DEMONIC
CITY STAGE.
THAT SEEMS
PRETTY SOLID.
( grunts )
OW!
DO I HAVE TO JUST
WAIT HERE FOR THE
NEXT TRANSITION?
HUH?
UH...
WHAT’S THIS?
AH, THANKS, I’M STARVING!
Sky Raker:
YOUR INCARNATION
TRAINING HAS BEGUN.
ASK YOURSELF WHY
YOU WEREN’T BLOWN AWAY
BY THE WIND YESTERDAY.
WHY WASN’T I...?
( gasps )
I’VE GOT IT!
INCARNATION IS ALL ABOUT
VISUALIZING YOUR WILL.
AT THAT MOMENT, I NEVER
THOUGHT FOR A SECOND
I’D BE BLOWN OFF.
OKAY. IF THAT’S HOW
THE INCARNATE SYSTEM
WORKS, THEN...
I’VE JUST GOT TO BELIEVE.
THIS IS NOTHING MORE
THAN A PROGRAM OBJECT.
WHICH MEANS...I SHOULD
BE ABLE TO BREAK IT!
( whimpering )
OW...
YES!
OKAY. NOW THINK.
VISUALIZE THAT YOUR FINGERS
AND ARM ARE A BLADE!
IT’S WORKING!
( grunting )
( sighs )
"GOOD LUCK, CROW."
THAT’S ALL SHE SAID?
NO INSTRUCTIONS
THIS MORNING?
WELL. I GUESS I HAVE TO ASSUME
THAT MEANS SHE’S ALREADY GIVEN
ME ALL THE INFORMATION I NEED.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
I’M MISSING, THOUGH...
Sky Raker:
REMEMBER...
THE POWER
TO VISUALIZE.
THAT IS THE TRUE POWER HIDDEN
WITHIN ALL BURST LINKERS.
Kuroyukihime:
HARUYUKI, YOU’RE
THE FASTEST THERE IS.
SOMEDAY...YOU’RE GOING
TO BE FASTER THAN ME
AND THE OTHER KINGS.
AND AS A BURST LINKER,
SPEED IS YOUR GREATEST POWER.
WAIT...THAT MEANS
WHEN KUROYUKIHIME
SENPAI TOLD ME THAT,
SHE MUST HAVE KNOWN ALL
ABOUT THE INCARNATE SYSTEM.
AND ACCORDING TO WHAT SHE
SAID, THE GREATEST POWER
ANYONE CAN HAVE IS SPEED.
SO I SHOULD BE VISUALIZING
SPEED, NOT POWER.
CREATE THE IMAGE
AND CONTROL IT.
IMAGINE SPEED AT ITS MAXIMUM.
GRASP IT, AND THEN MAKE IT REAL!
YES!
Sky Raker:
DO YOUR BEST!
COME ON.
( grunts )
LET’S KEEP GOING.
THIS TIME...TO THE VERY TOP!
Sky Raker: FROM THE BEGINNING,
MY AVATAR HAD ITS OWN
SPECIFIC ENHANCED ARMAMENT.
WITH JUST A QUICK BURST
OF PROPULSION,
I COULD LEAP FROM
THE GROUND AND JUMP
100 METERS INTO THE AIR.
BUT BEFORE LONG, THE DESIRE
TO SOAR EVEN HIGHER HAD
COMPLETELY CONSUMED ME.
I FOUGHT DUELS FOR THE SOLE
PURPOSE OF INCREASING MY
AVATAR’S JUMPING ABILITY.
AND BEFORE LONG,
I HAD REACHED LEVEL 8,
BUT THEN I REALIZED...
JUMPING WOULD NEVER BE THE SAME
AS FLYING, AND THAT’S THE MOMENT
MY DESIRE BECAME AN OBSESSION.
IT DROVE ME
COMPLETELY INSANE.
AND IN THE MIDST OF
THIS INSANITY, I DID
SOMETHING VERY FOOLISH.
IN AN ATTEMPT TO LIGHTEN MY
AVATAR AND STRENGTHEN MY WILL,
I DECIDED TO RID MYSELF
OF MY MOST VALUABLE
WEAPON...MY OWN LEGS.
SO WHAT I DID NEXT WAS TURN
TO THE MASTER OF MY LEGION,
A CLOSE FRIEND AND THE
ONLY PERSON I KNEW WHO
UNDERSTOOD MY OBSESSION,
AND ASKED HER TO
CUT THEM OFF WITH HER BLADES.
WAIT A SEC.
WAS THIS FRIEND...?
IT WAS BLACK LOTUS.
SHE WAS STRONGER AND MORE
HONORABLE THAT ANYONE.
BUT SHE WAS ALSO VERY KIND.
MY ONE TRUE
AND ONLY FRIEND.
SHE DID HER
BEST TO STOP ME.
BUT ALL I DID IN RETURN
WAS SAY HORRIBLE,
UNFORGIVABLE THINGS TO HER.
UNTIL EVENTUALLY, WITH A
LOOK ON HER FACE SO SAD
THAT I WILL NEVER FORGET IT,
SHE GRANTED MY REQUEST.
IN THE END, I WAS ABLE
TO REACH A HEIGHT OF 350 METERS.
JUST ENOUGH TO REACH
THE TOP OF THIS PLACE,
THE OLD TOKYO TOWER.
AND THEN I REALIZED SOMETHING:
SEEING THE SKY AT THE PEAK
OF MY TRAJECTORY,
FOR ONLY A BRIEF INSTANT,
IS THE ABSOLUTE LIMIT
OF MY POWERS.
Haru: BUT I...
( gasping )
I WANT TO GO HIGHER!
I WANT TO FLY...
TO THE ENDS OF THE EARTH!
( panting )
Sky Raker:
WELCOME BACK,
MR. CROW.
YOU MANAGED TO RETURN
MUCH SOONER THAN I
EXPECTED YOU TO.
NO WONDER SHE
CHOSE YOU.
I SHOULDN’T HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO MAKE
THAT DISTANCE...
BUT SOMEHOW,
I JUST KNEW
THAT I WOULD.
IF THAT’S THE POWER OF
INCARNATION, IT’S MORE THAN
JUST OPERATING AN AVATAR.
IT WAS LIKE
OVERRIDING
REALITY ITSELF!
EXACTLY.
"OVERRIDE."
YOU RESHAPED REALITY.
AND THAT’S THE ONE
WORD YOU NEED TO KNOW.
THE KEY TO INCARNATION.
"OVERRIDE."
ORIGINALLY, VISUALIZATION
CONTROL WAS JUST MEANT
TO BE A SUPPORT TOOL.
BUT AFTER A WHILE,
AS THE IMAGES BECAME
FASTER AND STRONGER,
THEY OVERRODE
THE CONSTRAINTS
OF THE PROGRAM.
IN OTHER WORDS, YOUR
WILL RESHAPES REALITY.
AND WITH THAT, I NO
LONGER HAVE ANYTHING
LEFT TO TEACH YOU.
BUT...I STILL CAN’T
REALLY DO ANYTHING!
I TOLD YOU...IN THE
END, I WAS NEVER ABLE
TO REACH THE SKY.
YEAH, BUT...
I WANNA FLY!
NO, IT’S MORE
THAN THAT.
I HAVE TO FLY AGAIN!
I HAVE TO DO IT
SO I CAN FIGHT
BESIDE HER!
DON’T WORRY.
I’M GOING TO GIVE
YOU SOME WINGS.
MY ENHANCED ARMAMENT,
GALE THRUSTER.
AND THEN WHAT?
I’M SURE YOU’LL BE
ABLE TO USE THOSE WINGS
TO REACH HEIGHTS
THAT I COULD HAVE
NEVER IMAGINED.
Sky Raker:
HELLO, MR. CROW.
OH, HI, GOOD MORNING!
MORNING.
SO, UM...HOW DID
YOU KNOW IT WAS ME?
I USED INCARNATION.
HUH?
I’M JOKING.
IT WASN’T
THAT HARD.
THERE AREN’T A WHOLE LOT OF
STUDENTS HANGING AROUND
THE OUTSIDE OF A FAST FOOD
RESTAURANT AT THIS TIME OF DAY.
( giggles )
Haru: LOOK I...
I JUST WANNA THANK YOU
FOR EVERYTHING YOU’VE DONE.
AND ALSO...THANKS FOR
COMING ALL THE WAY HERE.
IT REALLY MEANS A LOT TO ME.
OF COURSE,
DON’T MENTION IT.
THE ONLY WAY TO EXCHANGE
ENHANCED ARMAMENTS
WITHOUT USING A SHOP
IS BY CABLE-LINKING
IN THE REAL WORLD.
Both: BURST LINK.
Haru: THE GALE THRUSTER.
IT’S AMAZING.
AM I REALLY GONNA BE
ABLE TO MASTER THIS THING?
( gasps )
Sky Raker:
BUT BEFORE LONG, THE DESIRE
TO SOAR EVEN HIGHER...
HAD COMPLETELY
CONSUMED ME.
HER LEGS...
SHE HAS PROSTHETIC LEGS.
THAT’S WHY SHE WANTED
TO FLY SO BADLY.
MY PROBLEMS ARE NOTHING
COMPARED TO WHAT SHE
HAS TO GO THROUGH.
AND YET SHE’S WILLING
TO GIVE UP HER WINGS
FOR SOMEONE AS
PATHETIC AS ME.
YOU HAVE
A KIND HEART.
I’M DON’T! THAT’S NOT
TRUE AT ALL. I’M SORRY.
NO!
STOP THIS.
DON’T CRY!
( sobbing )
LISTEN,
MR. CROW.
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
I DIDN’T AGREE TO
HELP YOU OUT BECAUSE
I PITY YOU, OKAY?
JUST AS I KNOW YOU WOULD NEVER
DO SOMETHING OUT OF PITY FOR ME.
THOSE TEARS ARE PROOF THAT YOU
WILL FIND SOME SORT OF TRUTH FOR
YOURSELF IN ACCELERATED WORLD.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
( giggles )
PEOPLE WHO USE BRAIN BURST
FOR THEIR OWN SELFISH GAINS,
TO CREATE OPPORTUNITIES FOR
THEMSELVES IN THE REAL WORLD,
THEY WOULD NEVER
SHED TEARS LIKE THAT.
FOR THOSE PEOPLE, DUELS
ARE JUST A WAY FOR
THEM TO ACQUIRE POINTS,
MAKING ACCELERATED WORLD
NOTHING MORE THAN A PLACE
TO HUNT AND HURT OTHERS.
BUT YOU AND ME,
WE KNOW BETTER.
WE KNOW IT’S A PLACE
WHERE MUCH MORE
CAN BE FOUND.
TRUTH, FRIENDSHIP,
LOVE...EVEN BONDS
CAN BE FORMED THERE.
AM I RIGHT?
YES.
YOU ARE.
AS YOU NOW KNOW, I DID
SOMETHING REALLY FOOLISH,
AND AS A RESULT,
I LOST A FRIEND.
THAT’S WHY I DON’T
EVER WANT YOU TO MAKE
THAT SAME KIND OF MISTAKE.
REALIZE WHAT’S TRULY
IMPORTANT TO YOU
AND FIGHT FOR IT.
FIGHT. FOR WHAT’S
TRULY IMPORTANT TO ME...
I WILL! AND...
THANKS AGAIN
FOR EVERYTHING.
OKAY, MISS RAKER. I WON’T
FORGET WHAT YOU TAUGHT ME.
AND SOON, I’M GONNA
FLY AGAIN WITH MY OWN POWER.
WHEN THAT HAPPENS, I’LL
COME BACK AND RETURN
YOUR WINGS TO YOU.
I PROMISE!
OKAY! WELL,
BEST OF LUCK,
MR. CROW.
THANKS A LOT!
SEE YA!
UM...
BY THE WAY...
THAT FRIEND OF YOURS,
I DON’T THINK THAT YOU’VE
LOST HER JUST YET.
I’M PRETTY SURE SHE’S
ACTUALLY WAITING.
WAITING FOR YOU
TO COME BACK AND RETURN.
( gasps,
giggles )
( chuckles )
♪
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE, "FRAGMENTATION."
WHEN THEIR FUTURE IS SHATTERED
AND ALL HOPE SEEMS LOST...
HARUYUKI RETURNS
TO FIGHT ONCE AGAIN.