( cheering )
HE WHAT?
HE QUIT THE KENDO CLUB?
HE DID.
I HAVE TO ADMIT,
IT REALLY CAUGHT ME OFF GUARD.
I JUST COULDN’T BELIEVE IT.
WELL, DID YOU ASK HIM WHY?
I TRIED.
BUT HE WOULDN’T TELL ME.
HE JUST SAID THAT HE HAD
SOMETHING ELSE HE HAD TO DO.
TAKKUN...
Hime: NOW,
LET’S GET THIS STARTED.
Taku: BLACK LOTUS,
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
DIDN’T YOU HEAR ME?
I SAID, "LET’S
GET THIS STARTED."
WAIT!
I JUST WANNA--
MAKE NO MISTAKE.
YOU’VE JUST BEEN STOPPED
BY A FELLOW BURST LINKER
AND CHALLENGED TO A DUEL.
YOU MUST ACCEPT
THIS CHALLENGE
AND FIGHT ME WITH
EVERYTHING YOU’VE GOT.
THOSE ARE THE RULES
THAT GOVERN THIS WORLD.
IF YOU’RE JUST
GONNA STAND THERE...
THEN I WILL ATTACK FIRST!
♪
Akira:
RIGHT NOW I’M CONSIDERING
ONE OF TWO POSSIBILITIES.
YOU’RE EITHER INCREDIBLY
CUNNING AND BUMPED INTO ME
INTENTIONALLY
TO EXPOSE MY REAL IDENTITY,
OR YOU’RE JUST
AN ENORMOUS KLUTZ.
Haru: YEAH, IT’S DEFINITELY
THE SECOND OPTION.
I HAVE TO SAY,
I FIND IT ODD
THAT SILVER CROW,
WHO FOR THE LAST TWO WEEKS
HAS HAD A 70% WIN RATE,
HAS SUDDENLY
FOUND HIMSELF IN SUCH
A PERILOUS POSITION.
YOU MEAN YOU’VE HEARD
ABOUT ME BEFORE?!
PLEASE DON’T
SPEAK OUT LOUD.
( gasps ) SORRY.
OF COURSE
I’VE HEARD OF YOU.
EVERYONE IN THE ACCELERATED
WORLD KNOWS YOUR NAME NOW.
THE ONLY FLYING AVATAR
WITH A SHARP MIND.
YEAH, WELL..
OR SO IT SEEMED.
IN THE VIRTUAL WORLD
YOU SEEM QUITE CLEVER,
DRIVEN BY A FIERCE PASSION.
BUT IN THE REAL WORLD,
YOU’RE NOT SO BRIGHT.
( sighs )
LOOK, YOU SUMMED
IT UP PERFECTLY.
I AM DUMB.
I DID SOMETHING
I SHOULDN’T HAVE.
I WENT AND LEVELED UP
EVEN THOUGH I ONLY
HAD 308 POINTS.
WELL, IF THAT’S
THE REASON YOU’RE
IN SUCH DIRE STRAIGHTS,
THEN I GUESS I CAN
CONCLUDE THAT YOU
ARE INDEED A KLUTZ.
EXACTLY!
I’M GLAD THAT WE BOTH
UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER!
I THINK...
WE’VE GOTTEN OFF
TO AN ODD START.
LET ME PROPERLY
INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM AQUA CURRENT.
I’LL HELP YOU.
AND I’LL MAKE SURE YOU
GET BACK TO 50 POINTS.
YOU CAN CALL ME CURRENT.
( gasps )
OK, GREAT!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
LET’S BEGIN.
I’LL REGISTER US
FOR A TAG TEAM MATCH.
ACCELERATE THE SECOND YOU
CONNECT TO THE GLOBAL NET.
UH, OK.
WE’LL START HERE
IN CHIYODA.
IF WE CAN REACH OUR TARGET
POINTS IN THIS AREA,
THEN MY JOB IS DONE.
IF NOT, WE’LL MOVE
ONTO THE AKIHABARA AREA
AND CONTINUE FROM THERE.
ANY QUESTIONS?
UH... UM, NO.
NOT REALLY.
WAIT.
SHOULD I APOLOGIZE FOR
GRABBING HER BOOBS EARLIER?
BUT I DIDN’T REALLY
FEEL ANYTHING,
SO MAYBE I WAS
GRABBING SOMETHING ELSE.
I CAN HEAR YOU.
WHAT?!
BURST LINK.
AND YES,
YOU DID GRAB THEM.
OH, MY GOD!
I’M SO SORRY!
YOU SHOULD REALLY
DO YOURSELF A FAVOR
AND LEARN TO CONTROL
YOUR THOUGHTS WHEN
YOU’RE CABLE LINKING.
I CAN HEAR EVERYTHING.
I’LL BE MORE CAREFUL.
LET’S SEE WHO WE SHOULD
CHALLENGE FIRST.
( gasps )
W-WAIT A SEC!
WHAT’RE YOU DOING?
THAT TEAM YOU PICKED IS ALREADY
AT LEVEL THREE AND FOUR.
YOU REALLY WANNA FIGHT THEM?!
YOU ARE AT LEVEL TWO,
AND AS YOU KNOW I’M LEVEL ONE,
SO WE SHOULD SELECT OPPONENTS
WHO TOTAL LEVEL SIX OR GREATER.
IF THE SUM OF THE LEVEL
DIFFERENCE IS THREE OR MORE,
YOU WON’T BE STRIPPED
OF ALL YOUR POINTS
EVEN IF YOU LOSE.
YEAH, I SEE THE LOGIC
IN THAT BUT...
WAIT! SO, IS THAT
WHY YOU DO THIS?
STAY AT LEVEL ONE
AND NEVER LEVEL UP
ANY HIGHER?
THAT’S ONE OF THE REASONS.
BUT THERE ARE OTHERS.
WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT,
I WILL REVEAL TO YOU
WHAT THOSE ARE.
OR MAYBE I WON’T.
IT ALL DEPENDS.
WHAT THE HECK
DOES THAT MEAN?
PERFECT.
SAND DUCT
AND NICKEL DOLL.
THESE TWO ARE
AT LEVEL THREE AND FOUR.
BUT BECAUSE THEY
EACH HAVE LOTS OF POINTS,
THEY SHOULD BE UP
FOR A HEAD-TO-HEAD BATTLE.
OKAY.
IF YOU CAN KEEP YOUR COOL
AND FIGHT TO THE BEST
OF YOUR ABILITY,
THEN WE SHOULD
BE ABLE TO WIN.
( gasps )
SHE TOOK SO MANY FACTORS
INTO CONSIDERATION
WHEN CHOOSING
THESE OPPONENTS,
IT’S LIKE SHE REALLY KNOWS
WHAT’S BEST FOR ME RIGHT NOW.
I’LL DO MY BEST!
I’M GLAD TO SEE
YOU’RE SO INVESTED.
BUT JUST FIGHT
LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO.
WE CAN’T LOSE THIS DUEL.
BUT REMEMBER
THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING’S NOT WINNING--
IT’S ENJOYING IT!
IT’S JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
THAT MY GUARDIAN TAUGHT ME.
THAT IT’S SUPER IMPORTANT
TO ALWAYS ENJOY
EVERY DUEL I HAVE.
CORRECT.
OK. LET’S BEGIN.
THE ROTTING FOREST STAGE,
HUH?
A WATER-TYPE.
JUST LIKE HER NAME.
HERE THEY COME.
( gasps )
WE’LL ENGAGE THEM DOWN THERE.
OKAY.
A TOXIC SWAMP?
WHAT A NASTY STAGE.
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING!
( grunts )
Hime:
WHAT’S WRONG?
THERE’S NO NEED TO HOLD BACK.
I’VE RECOVERED ENOUGH POINTS NOW
THAT EVEN IF I LOSE TO YOU,
I’LL BE FINE.
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE
TO EARN A LOT OF POINTS.
PERHAPS THE TRUTH IS THAT THIS
IS THE BEST YOU’VE GOT.
I ASKED A MESSENGER
FROM LEONIDS ABOUT YOU.
I HEARD YOU PULLED OUT
OF THE KENDO TOURNAMENT.
WHY?
( sighs )
TO PUNISH MYSELF.
FOR WHAT?
BECAUSE I DID
SOMETHING WRONG.
I DON’T DESERVE
TO REMAIN HERE.
NOT LIKE THIS.
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
YOU WANT TO TAKE ALL
THAT YOU HAVE EARNED
AND ACQUIRED
AND THROW IT AWAY.
TO PAY FOR YOUR MISTAKE
BY GIVING UP EVERYTHING.
ONCE YOU’VE HELPED HARUYUKI
BECOME A BURST LINKER
WHO CAN HOLD HIS
OWN IN ANY FIGHT
YOU PLAN TO GET RID
OF BRAIN BURST DON’T YOU?
YOU PLAN TO UNINSTALL
IT YOURSELF.
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
IT’S THE ONLY
THING I CAN DO.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN
AFTER THAT?
WHAT ABOUT HARUYUKI?
AND KURASHIMA?
WHO RIGHT NOW IS DESPERATELY
TRYING TO FORGIVE YOU.
YOU’RE TAKING
THEIR FEELINGS
AND STOMPING
ALL OVER THEM.
THEN TELL ME WHAT
OTHER CHOICE DO I HAVE?
WHAT ELSE CAN I DO?!
HMM. FINALLY,
A REAL FIGHT.
( panting )
Nickel Doll:
WELL, NOW...
YOU’VE GOT SOME
NERVE BARGING IN HERE
AND CHALLENGING US
AT YOUR LEVEL.
Haru: SORRY.
I’LL HANDLE SAND DUCT.
YOU TAKE NICKEL DOLL.
SHE CAN EMIT ELECTRIC CURRENTS
FROM HER HANDS.
SO WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON’T LET HER CATCH YOU.
HEY, DON’T BE GIVIN’
AWAY MY TRICKS!
SAND BLAST!
I AM YOUR OPPONENT.
( grunts )
( gasps, moans )
HEY, LET GO!
HOW’D THAT FEEL, HUH?
THAT WASN’T NICE.
THROWING ME HEAD FIRST
INTO THIS MUCK.
YA’ GREAT BIG BULLY!
BULLY?!
SHOULDN’T YOU BE WORRIED?
I MEAN AFTER ALL,
YOU ARE STANDING
IN A TOXIC SWAMP.
IT’S GONNA CAUSE
SOME SERIOUS DAMAGE.
I’M AT LEVEL FOUR,
MY HP WILL LAST WAY
LONGER THAN YOURS.
POISON DOESN’T
AFFECT SILVER!
CRAP, THAT’S RIGHT!
YOUR COLOR STANDS
ON THE FAR LEFT
OF THE METAL CHART.
YES, OF COURSE,
YOU’RE SILVER.
( laughing )
SO?
YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY SHOULD
STUDY UP A BIT MORE
ON THAT COLOR OF YOURS.
SILVER IS RESISTANT
TO POISON BUT...
IT CONDUCTS ELECTRICITY
BETTER THAN ANY OTHER METAL!
AHH!
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
SILVER IS FOUR TIMES MORE
CONDUCTIVE THAN NICKEL,
SO THIS WILL BE OVER
IN NO TIME.
( groaning )
( grunting )
( gasps )
SO THAT’S THE AVIATION ABILITY!
DIVE ATTACK!
DID YOU WIN?
NO, NOT YET.
THAT WAS A NICE MOVE.
POWERFUL AND ELEGANT.
BUT THE OUTCOME
HAS ALREADY BEEN DECIDED.
AND YOU WILL NOT BE THE WINNERS.
SPLASH STINGER!
TELL ME WHAT I SHOULD DO!
HOW ELSE CAN I
RIGHT MY WRONGS?
WHAT CHOICE DO I HAVE?
( groans )
LET’S BE HONEST HERE,
SHALL WE?
YOU DON’T REALLY WANT TO ATONE
BY UNINSTALLING BRAIN BURST.
BUT AS LONG AS YOU HAVE
THE BRAIN BURST PROGRAM
YOU FEEL GUILTY
ABOUT WHAT YOU DID
AND YOU HATE
YOURSELF FOR THAT.
NO, IT’S NOT THAT.
HARUYUKI HOLDS NO
GRUDGE AGAINST YOU
AND THE MORE KURASHIMA
TRIES TO ACT LIKE
NOTHING HAS HAPPENED
THE MORE GUILT IT CAUSES.
YOU HATE THE FACT THAT
YOU HAD TO BE FORGIVEN.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
WHAT YOU HATE MOST,
IS BEING IMPERFECT.
THAT’S NOT IT.
THE PROBLEM IS YOU’RE
TOO SELF INVOLVED.
YOU’RE TRYING
TO PUNISH YOURSELF
INSTEAD OF JUST
OWNING YOUR MISTAKE.
YOU’RE WRONG!
AM I?
YOU’RE WRONG.
YOU DON’T KNOW ME AT ALL.
TAKE IT BACK!
SAND BLAST!
YOU TWO ARE FORGETTING
THE MOST IMPORTANT PART
OF A TAG TEAM MATCH.
THAT YOU AND YOUR PARTNER
MUST WORK TOGETHER.
YOU’RE NOT ATTACKING AS A TEAM.
IT DOESN’T MATTER HOW STRONG
YOU ARE AS INDIVIDUALS.
THAT’S NOT WHAT MATTERS
IN A TAG TEAM FIGHT.
YOU’RE RIGHT.
AND THAT’S WHY...
THIS BATTLE HASN’T
BEEN DECIDED YET.
( gasps )
UP UNTIL NOW,
ALL THE TAG TEAM MATCHES
I’VE BEEN FIGHTING
HAVE BEEN WITH MY BEST FRIEND.
SO, I GET IT.
I KNOW THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
TO DO IN A DUEL LIKE THIS
IS TO BELIEVE IN EACH OTHER.
AND THE PERSON I BELIEVE
IN IS MISS CURRENT.
LISTEN TO HIM,
TRYING TO SOUND ALL COOL!
ALL RIGHT, SANDY,
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE BLOW THESE LOSERS AWAY
WITH OUR ULTRA GORGEOUS
SPECIAL MOVE?
LET’S DO IT!
HERE COMES
THEIR JOINT ATTACK.
BE READY.
OK. HUH?
WHERE’RE YOU GOING?!
WELL WE CAN’T LET THEM TAKE US
BOTH OUT, CAN WE?
I’LL WATCH
AND IF YOU NEED ME
I’LL HELP OUT.
COME ON! DIDN’T YOU HEAR
A WORD I JUST SAID?!
ABOUT TAG TEAMS
WORKING TOGETHER?!
TURBO...
MOLECULAR!
HE’S ABSORBING THE WIND
HE GENERATED THROUGH HIS ARMS!
BUT FOR WHAT?
WHAT IS THIS?
THE TURBINES IN HIS ARMS
ARE DISPERSING THE MOLECULES
IN THE AIR
AND CREATING A VACUUM.
THE WIND ITSELF
IS NOT HARMFUL,
BUT IT’LL DRAG YOU IN
FOR CLOSE RANGE COMBAT.
SO THAT’S THEIR PLAN.
WAIT A SEC.
BUT IF I CAN GET IN CLOSE
AND LAND A GOOD KICK THEN...
HERE GOES!
AHH!
IDIOT!
ANODE CATHODE!
AHH!
HOW’S SHE DOING THIS?
SHE’S NOT TOUCHING ME
AND THERE’S NO WATER AROUND.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME AND
SANDY’S ULTRA GORGEOUS ATTACK?
MAYBE IT’S NOT AS GOOD
AS THAT PURPLE LADY’S ATTACK,
BUT IT’S PRETTY DANG CLOSE.
( continues yelling )
A GLOW DISCHARGE...
WHEN VOLTAGE MEETS ELECTRODES,
PLASMA IS FORMED.
WITH ENOUGH LOW PRESSURE,
ELECTRICITY IS CONDUCTED
AND FLOWS THROUGH THE AIR.
BETTER JUMP IN SOON OR YOU WON’T
HAVE ANY CLIENT LEFT TO SAVE!
BUT WITH THAT BODY, I DON’T KNOW
WHAT HELP YOU’RE GONNA BE.
I’M SURE HARUYUKI
HAS MENTIONED WHAT
HE WANTS FROM YOU.
WHY WON’T YOU LISTEN?
BECAUSE...
SHOULDN’T LISTENING
TO HIS WISH,
BE THE FIRST THING YOU DO?
( screams )
Hime:
HARUYUKI TOLD ME
THAT YOU ARE HIS BEST FRIEND!
( grunts )
JUST GIVE UP.
YOU’RE HP IS WAY TOO LOW
TO MAKE A COMEBACK NOW.
NEVER!
( grunts )
I CAN’T.
I WON’T LOSE THIS.
TAKU, MY BEST FRIEND,
WE’RE WIPING THE SLATE CLEAN!
SO I HAVE TO...
KEEP FIGHTING!
IT’S OVER.
Sand Duct: NICKY.
HUH?
( gasps )
THAT’S IMPOSSIBLE.
WATER SHOULD CONDUCT
ELECTRICITY.
MY BODY IS COMPOSED OF WATER
WITH NO IMPURITIES.
AND AS WATER THEORY STATES,
TRULY PURE WATER
IS A PERFECT INSULATOR.
DAMN IT!
YOU DOUCHEBAGS!
THE MOST IMPORTANT PART
OF A TAG TEAM MATCH...
IS ALWAYS TEAMWORK.
WHY DO YOU THINK LEGIONS EXIST
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD?
BECAUSE COMPETING WITH YOUR
FRIENDS AND SUPPORTING THEM
OPENS UP ALL SORTS
OF POSSIBILITIES.
YOU’VE ALWAYS
FOUGHT BY YOURSELF.
YOU’VE NEVER EXPERIENCED
THE TRUE JOY
FIGHTING WITH A TEAM PROVIDES.
TRY IT AND YOU WILL SEE,
THE POSSIBILITIES
ARE LIMITLESS.
( yelling )
Hime: THAT IS HOW YOU SHOULD
ATONE FOR YOUR MISTAKES.
YOUR POINTS ARE
BACK UP TO 54.
MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR ALL THE HELP.
THE PLEASURE WAS ALL MINE.
THANKS TO YOU,
I WAS ABLE TO LEARN
SEVERAL NEW BURST LINKER’S
TRICKS I DIDN’T KNOW BEFORE.
SO, DO YOU ALWAYS
HANG OUT AROUND HERE?
HMM? WHY?
WELL, IT’S JUST...
I THOUGHT THAT MAYBE WE
COULD MEET AGAIN SOMETIME.
( laughs )
WE WON’T BE
MEETING AGAIN.
HUH?
I CHOSE THIS PLACE
BECAUSE VERY FEW
BURST LINKER’S COME HERE.
WHICH MAKES IT EASIER FOR ME
TO COLLECT MY BONUS PAYMENT.
BONUS PAYMENT?!
I WASN’T TOLD OF SUCH--
( no audible dialogue )
AND NOW, I’M GOING TO STRIP
YOU OF ALL YOUR POINTS.
I CAN INITIATE
CONSECUTIVE DUELS
AS LONG AS YOU HAVEN’T
UNPLUGGED THE CABLE.
I INTEND TO KEEP
FIGHTING YOU UNTIL ALL
YOUR POINTS ARE GONE.
UH...
SO, IS THIS
YOUR BONUS PAYMENT?
OF COURSE.
THERE’S NO POINT IN BEING
A BOUNCER OTHERWISE.
NOW, GET READY.
I WANT YOU TO SHOW ME
EVERYTHING YOU’VE GOT.
EVERY LAST DROP.
( gasps )
WHAT?
AREN’T YOU AT LEAST
GOING TO TRY?
I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
I TRUST YOU.
FROM THE VERY
FIRST MOMENT WE MET,
I BELIEVED YOU WERE
A GOOD PERSON.
SEE, I HAD A REALLY
INTENSE DUEL
WITH A GOOD FRIEND
OF MINE RECENTLY.
I LET MY ANGER
AND PAIN TAKEOVER
AS WE FOUGHT.
I REALLY HATED HIM
IN THAT BATTLE.
BUT...
IN THE END I WAS ABLE
TO TRUST HIM AGAIN.
AND I MADE UP MY MIND.
I DECIDED THAT ONCE
I CHOOSE TO BELIEVE
IN SOMEONE,
I WILL NEVER LET THAT GO.
I WILL ALWAYS
BELIEVE IN THEM.
SO, YOU WON’T FIGHT ME?
I WON’T GO UP AGAINST
SOMEONE THAT I BELIEVE IN.
I WAS JUST LYING.
I WANTED TO SCARE YOU A BIT
SINCE YOU’RE SO UNGUARDED.
BUT THAT DIDN’T
SEEM TO WORK.
NO, IT DID.
( crying ) YOU SCARED
THE CRAP OUT OF ME!
( chuckles )
HUH?
A LONG TIME AGO,
I HAD FRIENDS TOO.
AND A MASTER I CARED ABOUT.
BUT SOMETHING HAPPENED
AND WE ALL WENT
OUR SEPARATE WAYS.
WOW. REALLY?
TREASURE YOU FRIENDS.
DON’T EVER FORGET THAT.
HUH?
WE WEREN’T
SUPPOSED TO MEET.
AT LEAST NOT YET.
YOU’VE JUST BEGUN.
YOU AND YOUR MASTER
HAVE A LONG JOURNEY
AHEAD OF YOU.
WE ELEMENTS SHOULDN’T
INTERVENE IN THAT.
THAT’S WHY I HAVE
TO DO THIS.
ERASE YOUR MEMORY OF ME.
DO WHAT?
MEMORY LEAK.
( groaning )
WAIT A SEC.
WHAT THE...
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHOSE CABLE IS THIS?
Taku’s Mom:
CHIYURI CAME BY
AND DROPPED OFF
SOME OF YOUR STUFF.
( grunts )
CHI...
Mom: SHE PUT THEM ON YOUR BED
AND THEN WENT STRAIGHT HOME.
HEY, MOM?
THERE’S SOMETHING
THAT I WANT TO TELL YOU.
MORNING!
OH.
HEY, GOOD MORNING.
WHY ARE YOU STILL
ACTING ALL WEIRD?
HUH?
LOOK, WHAT’S DONE
IS DONE, OKAY?
OR MAYBE YOU’RE LOOKING
FOR A CHANCE TO BUY
ME MORE ICE CREAM?
CHIYU...
Taku:
YOU HEARD HER, HARU.
( both gasp )
MORNING GUYS.
THAT UNIFORM
HE’S WEARING.
IT’S ONE
OF OUR UNIFORMS.
Chiyu and Haru:
WHAT?!
Taku:
THANK YOU.
Hime: GLASSES?
IN THIS DAY AND AGE?
NEURO-LINKER’S VISION CORRECTION
HAS PRETTY MUCH MADE GLASSES
A THING OF THE PAST.
I’VE DECIDED...
I WANT TO SEE THINGS WITH
MY OWN EYES FROM NOW ON.
I WANT TO SEE
THE REAL CHI...
AND HARU.
AS WELL AS MYSELF.
( chuckles )
THEY SUIT YOU.
WAIT!
HMM?
TELL ME...
I’M CURIOUS AS TO HOW
YOU HAPPENED TO KNOW
SO MUCH ABOUT ME?
I DON’T REALLY.
HUH?
BUT AS I THINK
YOU MAY KNOW,
I ALSO COMMITTED AN ACT ONCE
THAT I CAN NEVER TAKE BACK.
THAT’S ALL.
THANK YOU, MY MASTER.
Haru:
HEY! TAKU!
( both giggling )
♪
NEXT STAGE, "TEMPTATION."
A YOUNG GIRL SUDDENLY
ENTERS HARUYUKI’S LIFE.
BUT WHAT DOES
SHE SEEK FROM HIM?