♪
Kuroyukihime:
MORNING, TAKUMU.
HUH?
OH, HI.
GOOD MORNING, MASTER.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND THAT
I’M YOUR LEGION MASTER,
BUT YOU REALLY DON’T NEED
TO CALL ME THAT ALL THE TIME.
OKAY, SORRY, BUT I’M AFRAID
THAT’S JUST WHAT COMES
MOST NATURALLY TO ME.
THAT LOOKS GOOD,
I BET CHIYU MADE IT.
SO WHY ARE YOU EATING HERE
ALONE IN THE COLD?
YOU GUYS SHOULD BE
EATING TOGETHER.
IT’S SUCH A NICE, SUNNY DAY.
I WANTED TO ENJOY IT.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD GET
MORE SUNSHINE YOURSELF, HARU.
ANYWAY,
UNLIKE YOU TWO LOVEBIRDS,
THINGS ARE COMPLICATED
BETWEEN CHIYU AND ME RIGHT NOW.
Both: IT’S NOT LIKE THAT!
SO, YOU SAID YOU HAD
SOMETHING TO TELL ME?
♪
Haru:
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK, TAKU?
HMM. WELL,
WITHOUT ANY MORE INFORMATION,
IT’S HARD TO GUESS WHAT
THE RED KING REALLY WANTS.
BUT I HAVE A PRETTY GOOD IDEA
OF WHAT SHE WOULD HAVE DONE
IF HARU HADN’T FIGURED OUT
HER TRUE IDENTITY.
OH?
REALLY? LIKE WHAT?
KNOWING YOU LIKE I DO, HARU,
I BET AFTER LIVING WITH HER
FOR THREE DAYS,
YOU’D HAVE GROWN
QUITE FOND OF HER.
THEN SHE’D SAY SOMETHING LIKE,
"TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I’M A BURST LINKER.
"BUT BECAUSE I’M SO YOUNG,
"EVERY TIME
I EARN ANY POINTS,
"ALL THE SENIOR MEMBERS
IN MY LEGION
"TAKE THEM AWAY FROM ME.
"I REALLY NEED YOUR HELP.
WON’T YOU PLEASE COME
TO MY LEGION AND PROTECT ME?"
AT LEAST, THAT’S MY GUESS.
THAT’S RIDICULOUS.
THAT TRAP’S SO OBVIOUS,
NO ONE WOULD BE
STUPID ENOUGH TO FALL FOR IT.
NOT EVEN HARUYUKI HERE
WOULD BELIEVE SOMETHING
LIKE THAT STOR--
( crying )
ARE YOU REALLY
THAT STUPID?!
BUT THAT POOR GIRL
BEING BULLIED LIKE THAT...
I AM WARNING YOU.
( groaning )
DON’T EVEN THINK ABOUT
DOING SOMETHING COOL
LIKE CHANGING LEGIONS
REAL QUICK.
YOU’RE NOT GOING
TO JUMP SIDES, RESCUE HER,
THEN COME BACK
WHEN YOU’RE DONE.
HUH? BUT WHY NOT?
BECAUSE OF
AN EXECUTION TECHNIQUE
CALLED THE JUDGMENT BLOW.
AAH!
A SPECIAL MOVE THAT IS GRANTED
ONLY TO LEGION MASTERS
FOR THE PURPOSE OF TERMINATION.
ANY LEGION MEMBER
WHO IS HIT BY THIS MOVE
INSTANTLY LOSES
OF ALL THEIR POINTS,
AS WELL AS BRAIN BURST FOREVER.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
IF YOU HAD JOINED
THE RED LEGION,
EVEN IF IT WAS
JUST FOR A LITTLE BIT,
THAT’D BE ENOUGH.
SHE’D HAVE HELD
THE POWER OF LIFE AND DEATH
OVER SILVER CROW FOREVER.
MOST LIKELY, HER PLAN
WAS TO THREATEN YOU
WITH THE JUDGMENT BLOW
TO GET YOU TO DO
SOME SORT OF BIDDING FOR HER.
BUT BECAUSE YOU
WERE ABLE TO BLOW HER COVER,
SHE’S NOW HOPING TO HAVING
A MEETING WITH YOUR MASTER
SO SHE CAN PROPOSE
SOME KIND OF DEAL DIRECTLY.
HMM.
WELL THEN, I THINK
WE SHOULD AT LEAST
HEAR WHAT SHE HAS TO SAY.
HARUYUKI, GO AHEAD
AND CALL THE RED KING.
SET UP A MEETING
FOR 4:00 P.M. TODAY.
TELL HER WE WILL ALL
MEET AT YOUR PLACE.
HUH?
Haru: ARE YOU SURE
WE CAN’T MEET SOMEWHERE ELSE?
I HAVEN’T MENTALLY
PREPARED MYSELF FOR THIS YET,
AND THE PLACE IS A TOTAL MESS.
YOU’RE SAYING IT’S OKAY
FOR THE RED KING, BUT NOT ME?
WELL, YOU GOT ME THERE.
( elevator dings )
I SHOULD HAVE ENOUGH DRINKS
AND SNACKS FOR EVERYONE.
SO THE ONLY
OTHER OBSTACLE IS...
MAKING SURE SHE DOESN’T SEE
THE HIDDEN GAME COLLECTION
IN MY ROOM!
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE,
DON’T LET ANYTHING GO WRONG!
( beeping )
( gasps )
Niko: DIE, SUCKERS!
BURN IN HELL!
AAH!
( video game sounds )
OH, HEY THERE. WELCOME BACK.
YOU’VE GOT SOME GREAT TASTE.
I LOVE THESE OLD GAMES!
I HAPPEN TO BE
A BIG FAN OF THEM AS WELL.
VIDEO GAMES FROM THIS ERA
HAD YET TO BE BURDENED
BY CENSORSHIPS.
YES! I CLEARED STAGE 5!
HEY! HOW DID YOU
GET INTO MY ROOM ANYWAY?!
I ALREADY TOLD YOU.
I GOT AN INSTANCE KEY
FROM YOUR MOM.
IT UNLOCKS
EVERYTHING AROUND HERE.
BUT DON’T WORRY...
I LEFT YOUR OTHER
PRIZED COLLECTION
HIDDEN BEHIND THE BOOKSHELF...
AS IS.
( sighs )
I’M DONE FOR.
SO, YOU’RE THE BLACK KING, HUH?
WHAT, DID YOU JUST COME BACK
FROM A FUNERAL?
I FELT A DARK CLOUD
COME OVER THE PLACE
AS SOON AS YOU WALKED IN.
AND YOU’RE JUST
A LITTLE RAY OF SUNSHINE.
IN FACT, I BET IF I
HUNG YOU FROM A STREET LIGHT,
YOU’D STOP TRAFFIC.
O-OKAY! T-THAT’S ENOUGH!
I’M SO LUCKY!
MY MOM’S OUT OF TOWN
AND I HAVE TWO PRETTY GIRLS
STANDING IN MY LIVING ROOM
WITH ME! ( laughs )
ARE YOU DONE?
YOU’RE SO FUCKIN’ DEAD!
AAH!
( doorbell rings )
( whimpers )
( sighs )
( chuckles )
T... TAKU! ( crying )
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE START THIS OFF
WITH SOME INTRODUCTIONS?
RED KING,
WHY DON’T YOU GO FIRST BY
TELLING US YOUR REAL NAME.
IT’S YUNIKO. YUNIKO KOZUKI.
LET’S CONFIRM THAT
WITH YOUR NAME TAG.
IT’S JUST FURTHER PROOF.
YOU CAN’T FORGE
A QUANTUM CODE KEY NAME TAG.
OKAY, FINE. HERE.
YUNIKO KOZUKI.
ALL RIGHT, CYAN PILE,
IT’S YOUR TURN NOW.
I’M TAKUMU MAYUZUMI.
TAKUMU MAYUZUMI.
HERE’S PROOF.
WELL, SHOW US
YOUR NAME TAG, TOO.
OKAY, BUT YOU ALREADY
KNOW MY REAL NAME.
HERE. HARUYUKI ARITA.
HARUYUKI ARITA.
HMM? OH, MY TURN?
KUROYUKIHIME.
AH, COME ON!
THAT ISN’T YOUR REAL NAME!
FINE, WHATEVER!
I’LL JUST THINK OF YOU
AS THAT ANNOYING GIRL
WHO THINKS SHE’S A PRINCESS.
AT LEAST I’M NOT SO ARROGANT
I TELL PEOPLE I’M A KING.
PISS OFF!
( grunts )
ALL RIGHT. SHALL WE
GET ON WITH IT THEN?
SO, RED KING...
THE FIRST THING I WANT TO KNOW
IS HOW YOU MANAGED TO FIND OUT
HARU’S REAL IDENTITY.
I WENT TO ALL
THE JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOLS
IN THE SUGINAMI AREA
AND APPLIED FOR
A VISITOR I.D. PASS.
THEN I LOGGED ONTO
EACH SCHOOL’S LOCAL NETWORK.
AND THEN WHAT?
IF YOU JUST LOGGED ONTO
UMESATO’S SCHOOL NET,
ALL YOU’D FIND ARE THE NAMES
OF ITS STUDENTS.
THEN I WAITED IN A PLACE
WHERE I HAD A CLEAR VIEW
OF THE SCHOOL GATES.
I’D SIT THERE AND WATCH
AS EACH STUDENT WAS LEAVING
THE SCHOOL GROUNDS.
THEN I’D ACCELERATE
AND CHECK THE MATCHING LIST.
WHEN SILVER CROW’S NAME
FINALLY POPPED UP ON THE LIST,
AND I REALIZED
IT WAS THIS GUY HERE
WHO WAS LEAVING THE SCHOOL,
LET’S JUST SAY I WAS MORE
THAN A LITTLE BIT SHOCKED.
SO THEN,
HOW MANY BURST POINTS
DID YOU END UP USING
FOR ALL THAT?
OVER 200.
200?!
SO WHAT IS IT
THAT MADE YOU WANT
TO MEET HARUYUKI THAT BADLY?
HAD YOU PERHAPS
FALLEN IN LOVE WITH HIM?
( gags ) HELL NO!
( grunts )
( groans )
I COULD COULDN’T CARE LESS
ABOUT THIS FATSO!
WHAT I WANT IS HIS AVATAR!
SILVER CROW...
I WANT TO BORROW YOUR WINGS...
YOUR ABILITY TO FLY...
JUST ONCE.
SO I CAN DESTROY
THE ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE.
ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE?
IMPOSSIBLE! THAT ARMOR
HAS ALREADY BEEN DESTROYED.
TWO AND A HALF YEARS AGO,
I WAS THERE.
I WITNESSED
THE END OF CHROME DISASTER
AND I CONFIRMED THE DESTRUCTION
OF THAT ARMOR MYSELF.
WELL, IF THAT’S THE CASE,
THEN EXPLAIN TO ME
WHY IT’S SHOWN UP AGAIN.
HOLD ON A SEC.
WHAT ARE YOU TWO TALKING ABOUT?
AND WHAT IS
THIS ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE
AND CHROME DISASTER ANYWAY?
OKAY, HARUYUKI.
WOULD YOU MIND
FINDING TWO CABLES FOR US
SO WE CAN ALL CABLE LINK?
IT’LL BE A LOT QUICKER
IF I JUST SHOW YOU.
THESE ARE THE ONLY
TWO CABLES I HAVE.
THIS ONE’S A METER LONG,
AND THIS ONE’S
ONLY 50 CENTIMETERS.
SORRY. UNFORTUNATELY,
I JUST BROUGHT ONE LONG CABLE
WITH ME TODAY.
( giggles ) I GET IT.
OKAY, FINE.
I’LL MAKE DO WITH
THE SUPER SHORT CABLE.
( gasps ) NO WAY!
ARE YOU JOKING?!
I’LL BE USING THAT CABLE!
( giggles )
YOU’RE TOO LATE!
WAIT! ( whimpers )
WHAT’RE YOU DOING?!
HURRY UP.
PLUG IN THAT LONG CABLE. OKAY?
AND THEN
HAND IT ON OVER TO HER.
BACK OFF!
DON’T GET SO CLOSE TO HIM!
I CAN’T HELP IT.
THIS CABLE IS JUST SO SHORT.
HMPH. FINE!
THIS IS WHY I HATE CHILDREN.
THINKING CABLE LENGTH
CAN EQUIVOCATE INTIMACY?
HOW IMMATURE!
YEAH, UM, I’LL JUST BE
USING THIS LONG ONE HERE.
SO, MASTER,
ARE WE GOING TO ACCELERATE?
NO. THERE’S NO NEED
TO DO THAT.
OPEN DIRECT LINK!
WHERE ARE WE?
( rumbling )
Haru: BLACK LOTUS?
WHAT YOU’RE SEEING
IS A VR MOVIE,
NOT THE ACCELERATED WORLD.
IT’S THE RECORDING OF A MEMORY
THAT HAPPENED TWO YEARS AGO.
I’M TRANSMITTING IT
FROM MY BRAIN TO YOURS.
LET ME GUESS, YOU’RE REPLAYING
THE FIGHT BETWEEN
THE SEVEN KINGS OF PURE COLOR
AND THE FOURTH CHROME DISASTER?
THE FOURTH ONE?
( rumbling )
HMM?
( whimpering )
THE NAME CHROME DISASTER
ORIGINATES FROM A LEGENDARY
BURST LINKER--
A PLAYER FROM SEVEN YEARS AGO,
DURING THE EARLY DAYS
OF ACCELERATED WORLD.
HE WAS SAID TO BE A RELENTLESS
AND BRUTAL FIGHTER.
HE USED UNMATCHED FIGHTING POWER
TO BRING ABOUT ABSOLUTE TYRANNY.
BUT EVENTUALLY, THE TIME CAME
FOR HIS RULE TO END.
THE HIGHEST LEVEL BURST LINKERS
OF THAT TIME
DECIDED TO ALL BAND TOGETHER,
AND THEY BROUGHT HIM DOWN.
BUT BEFORE HE MET HIS DEMISE
IN ACCELERATED WORLD,
HE SCREAMED A FINAL STATEMENT.
"THIS IS NOT THE END.
"THE CURSE
I PLACE ON THIS WORLD
WILL KEEP ME COMING BACK
TO PLAGUE YOUR FOR ETERNITY!"
HE WAS TELLING THE TRUTH.
EVEN THOUGH HE HAD VANISHED
FROM THE ACCELERATED WORLD,
HIS ENHANCED ARMAMENT,
THE ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE,
REMAINED.
ENHANCED ARMAMENT?
THAT’S WHAT WE CALL
OUR EXTERNAL ITEMS.
MY ARMORED FORTRESS AND GUN
BOTH FALL UNDER THAT AS WELL.
AN ENHANCED ARMAMENT
IS TYPICALLY NOTHING MORE
THAN AN ITEM.
IT HAS NO WILL OF ITS OWN.
BUT THE ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE
WAS DIFFERENT.
( gasping )
IT SOMEHOW POSSESSED
ONE OF THE BURST LINKERS
WHO TOOK PART IN THE EXECUTION.
IN THE COURSE OF ONE NIGHT,
IT COMPLETELY TOOK OVER
THE PLAYER’S MIND,
AND TRANSFORMED HIM
INTO A BRUTAL MONSTER.
THIS SCENARIO REPEATED ITSELF
THREE MORE TIMES.
EVEN WHEN THE POSSESSED LINKER
WAS DESTROYED,
THE ARMOR NEVER DISAPPEARED.
IT WOULD SIMPLY
POSSESS ANOTHER PLAYER
AND CORRUPT THEM AS WELL.
THIS HERE...
...WAS THE FOURTH
CHROME DISASTER.
♪
( roars )
( whimpers )
THAT THING LOOKS ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING LIKE THE FIFTH ONE
WHO’S ON A RAMPAGE RIGHT NOW.
THE ARMOR CHANGES ITS SHAPE
TO SUIT THE PLAYER’S AVATAR.
BUT THE CRAZED AND MANIC STYLE
OF ATTACKS NEVER CHANGE.
Taku: THAT’S THE GREEN KING,
GREEN GRANDEE.
HIS ABSOLUTE DEFENSE ABILITY
HAS EARNED HIM THE TITLE
"THE INVULNERABLE."
Niko: THEY SAY HE’S ROCK SOLID.
( roars )
SENPAI, IS THAT ACTUALLY
A BURST LINKER I’M SEEING?
A REAL PERSON, JUST LIKE US,
IS INSIDE THAT CRAZY THING?
( gasps )
Haru: IS IT WOUNDED?
Kuroyukihime: YES.
HE HAS ALREADY WENT UP
AGAINST THE OTHER KINGS
AND IS NOW
ON THE VERGE OF DEATH.
YET AS YOU CAN SEE,
IT’S STILL RAGING.
( roars )
LOOK OUT!
( gasps )
Kuroyukihime:
THAT WASN’T THE END OF IT.
IT CONTINUED FIGHTING LIKE THAT
UNTIL IT FINALLY DIED.
AFTER THAT LAST BATTLE,
THE OTHER KINGS AND MYSELF
CONFIRMED THAT
THE ARMOR WAS GONE,
THAT IT NO LONGER EXISTED
IN OUR DATA STORAGE.
THE CURSE SHOULD HAVE BEEN
BROKEN FOR GOOD AT THAT POINT.
YEAH, WELL,
THEN HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
WHAT’S HAPPENING RIGHT NOW?
THE FACT THAT THERE’S
A FIFTH ONE OUT THERE
WREAKING HAVOC EVERYWHERE
EVEN AS WE SPEAK!
SO WHICH KING FELL VICTIM?
WHO IS THE FIFTH ONE?
IT’S NOT A KING.
HE’S ONE OF MY OWN.
SEE, HE’S A MEMBER
OF THE RED LEGION, PROMINENCE.
HE WAS CALLED CHERRY ROOK.
AND HE WAS A REALLY GOOD GUY.
HE DIDN’T HAVE
ANY FLASHY ABILITIES,
BUT HE MADE IT TO LEVEL 6
THROUGH HARD WORK.
HE HAD ALL KINDS OF THINGS
GOIN’ FOR HIM.
BUT NOW... DAMN IT!
HE’S STILL A MEMBER
OF THE RED LEGION.
BUT HE’S CONSTANTLY ATTACKING
THE MEMBERS OF OTHER LEGIONS.
HE’S BREAKING
THE NON-AGGRESSION TREATY.
SO I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I HAVE TO FINISH HIM.
THE JUDGMENT BLOW.
YEAH. BUT I CAN’T GET TO HIM.
THE JUDGMENT BLOW
IS A CLOSE RANGE MOVE.
YOU’VE GOTTA BE
RIGHT NEXT TO THEM.
BUT THIS GUY’S LEAPING POWER
IS TOTALLY OFF THE CHARTS.
HE CAN EASILY JUMP UP
AND ESCAPE ME.
AND HE HAS
AWESOME CONTROL OF IT.
IT’S ALMOST LIKE HE’S FLYING.
I SEE. WELL, AT LEAST
WE FINALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU ARE AFTER.
HUH? WE DO?
WE REALLY KNOW WHAT SHE WANTS?
ISN’T IT OBVIOUS?
IT’S BECAUSE I NEED YOUR HELP.
I WANT YOU TO CATCH
CHROME DISASTER FOR ME.
HUH? WHAT?! NO!
THAT’S INSANE, I CAN’T DO THAT!
IT’LL BE A GOOD EXPERIENCE.
I THINK THAT YOU SHOULD TRY
AND GIVE IT A GO.
HUH?!
IT’S DANGEROUS, MASTER.
IT COULD ALSO BE A TRAP.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP IN MIND
THAT OUR GOAL IS LEVEL 10.
WHICH MEANS THAT
ALL OTHER KINGS ARE OUR ENEMIES,
PEOPLE WE’LL EVENTUALLY
HAVE TO DESTROY.
WHAT’S YOUR PROBLEM, KID?
AND HEY, NICE SPECS.
SO, DO THEY
CALL YOU TEACH?
( sighs )
I MADE CONTACT WITH YOU GUYS
FACE-TO-FACE.
IF I DID BETRAY YOU,
THEN YOU COULD EASILY
COME AND GET ME IN REAL LIFE
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
TRUE. IT’S A LITTLE RISKY,
BUT IT DOES HAVE ITS UPSIDE.
I SUPPOSE YOU HAVE SOMETHING
TO SWEETEN THE DEAL?
SOMETHING WE GET IN RETURN?
YEAH, OF COURSE.
I’LL TELL MY CREW
THEY’RE TO LEAVE YOU ALONE
IN SUGINAMI.
AT LEAST FOR THE TIME BEING.
THEN WE’VE GOT A DEAL.
SO, WHEN AND WHERE
CAN THIS PLAYER BE FOUND?
I’M WORKING ON
PINPOINTING HIS LOCATION.
WE’LL KNOW
BEFORE TOMORROW NIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
AFTER SCHOOL TOMORROW,
WE MEET BACK UP HERE.
UH, DON’T I GET A SAY IN THIS?
Taku: NIGHT, HARU.
Haru: YEAH, NIGHT.
SEE YOU TOMORROW, HARUYUKI.
WAIT.
WHY DON’T I WALK YOU HOME?
IT’S PRETTY LATE.
NO, I’LL BE FINE.
SEE YA LATER, PRINCESS.
OKAY, NOW LET’S
GET BACK TO THE GAME!
HOLD ON! NOT SO FAST, KID!
WHAT NOW?
SURELY YOU’RE NOT PLANNING
TO SPEND ANOTHER NIGHT HERE,
ARE YOU?
OF COURSE I AM.
YOU DON’T EXPECT ME TO GO HOME
EVERY TIME, DO YOU?
WHAT A PAIN.
AND BESIDES, THE SCHOOL I GO TO
IS A BOARDING SCHOOL.
I FORGED A 3-DAY EXIT PASS.
SO EVEN IF I DO GO BACK,
THEY WON’T HAVE ANY FOOD FOR ME.
AND SPEAKING OF FOOD,
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO HAVE
FOR DINNER TONIGHT, HUH?
( giggles )
I... I...
THAT GOODBYE I SAID EARLIER...
WELL, I TAKE IT BACK!
I’M STAYING THE NIGHT, TOO!
( whimpering )
LET’S SEE NOW,
ANY GOOD DEALS GOING ON TODAY?
CABBAGES, BURDOCK...
HOW ABOUT THIS?
BLACK SQUID INK NOODLE?!
WHY WOULD I WANT TO EAT
SOMETHING AS DISGUSTING
AS THAT?!
OH, MY APOLOGIES.
FOR THE RED KING,
SOME RED CHILI NOODLES?
NO! GIVE IT UP!
WHAT’S WITH ALL THIS
INSTANT NOODLE CRAP ANYWAY?
DO NEITHER OF YOU TWO
THINK THAT I CAN COOK?
I WANT MEATLOAF TONIGHT!
( giggles )
HEY, YOU GUYS OKAY
WITH MEATLOAF, TOO?
YUNIKO...
Niko: "YUNIKO’S ALL ALONE
IN HER BOARDING SCHOOL.
I BET SHE’S WANTS HER PARENTS
TO SPOIL HER JUST LIKE
THAT OTHER GIRL."
I REALLY HOPE
YOU’RE NOT THINKING
SOMETHING STUPID LIKE THAT.
UH, WELL, UM... SORT OF.
YOU’LL FIND THIS OUT
FOR YOURSELF SOON ENOUGH.
YOU SEE, THE MORE TIME
YOU SPEND PLAYING BRAIN BURST,
THE LESS YOU CARE ABOUT
YOUR LIFE IN THE REAL WORLD.
IF YOU KNEW JUST HOW MUCH TIME
THIS CHICK AND ME HAVE SPENT IN
THE ACCELERATED WORLD,
I’M TELLING YA,
IT WOULD BLOW YA AWAY.
YOU MEAN YOUR
TOTAL PLAYING TIME?
WHAT IS IT?
I’M NOT TELLIN’.
WHY DON’T YOU TRY
AND WORK IT OUT BY YOURSELF.
AND HEY,
DON’T EVER CALL ME YUNIKO.
IT MAKES MY DAMN SKIN CRAWL.
NIKO IS FINE. JUST CALL ME NIKO
AND WE’LL BE GOOD.
BUT STAY AWAY FROM ANY
STUPID, CUTESY NICKNAMES!
( shower running )
Niko: HEY, HURRY UP
AND WASH MY BACK.
Kuroyukihime:
WHAT? DO IT YOURSELF.
Niko: SHUT UP, JUST DO IT.
OKAY, LET’S SORT THIS THROUGH.
MY MOM IS OUT OF TOWN
AND I’VE GOT
TWO GIRLS STAYING HERE...
MAKING ME FOOD...
AND BATHING TOGETHER.
THINK.
WHAT’S A GUY SUPPOSED TO DO
AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
IF THIS WERE AN ANIME
OR SOME GAME,
IT’D USUALLY GO LIKE...
( giggles )
AFTER THE FAN SERVICE, THE BOY
ASKS IF THE WATER’S HOT ENOUGH,
AND THEN ACCIDENTALLY STUMBLES
INTO THE BATHROOM.
THAT’S WHEN THE GIRLS,
BARELY DRESSED,
THROW SHAMPOO AND OTHER STUFF
AT THE BOY TO CHASE HIM OUT.
IN OTHER WORDS,
FOLLOWING THAT EXAMPLE
WOULD BE THE MOST
OPTIMAL SOLUTION FOR ME, RIGHT?
AAH!
AHH.
ALL RIGHT! POPSICLES!
( gasps )
STOP STARING AT ME LIKE THAT.
I HAD TO GET THIS COLOR.
IT’S ALL THEY HAD IN MY SIZE.
N-NO, IT’S NOT LIKE THAT!
IT REALLY SUITS YOU!
IT’S PERFECT!
LIKE, A TOTAL HIT!
HEY, SILVER CROW,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HUH?
GET THIS, WHEN SHE’S NAKED,
YOU’D BE SURPRISED AT HOW--
( groans )
HEY! WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING ANYWAY?
( giggles )
THIS ALL YOU’VE GOT, RED KING?
OH, NO,
’CAUSE I’M ABOUT TO CRUSH YOU.
( giggles )
( chuckles )
( grunts )
( snoring )
Taku: YOU HAVE TO KEEP IN MIND
THAT OUR GOAL IS LEVEL 10.
WHICH MEANS THAT ALL
OTHER KINGS ARE OUR ENEMIES,
PEOPLE WE’LL EVENTUALLY
HAVE TO DESTROY.
♪
Kuroyukihime: THE TEAM SETS OUT
ON THEIR FIRST MISSION INSIDE
THE UNLIMITED NEUTRAL FIELD.
WHAT DANGER AWAITS THEM
IN THIS NEW WORLD?