Haru voice over: ( gasps )
WHAT WAS THAT LAG ABOUT?
HOLD ON! THIS IS
A BACK DOOR PROGRAM!
WAIT...
WHOEVER DID THIS IS
PROBABLY WATCHING
WHAT I’M DOING RIGHT NOW.
FOR THE TIME BEING, THE BEST
THING FOR ME TO DO IS NOTHING.
PRETEND LIKE I NEVER NOTICED.
( sighs )
Chiyuri voice over:
HEY, HARU...
IF KUROYUKIHIME CAN GIVE YOU
WHAT YOU WANT. HELP YOU CHANGE.
THEN I WON’T GET
IN THE WAY.
BUT PLEASE.
STOP LETTING
HER BOSS YOU AROUND.
( grunts )
IF YOU CAN BE
HER BOYFRIEND,
THEN DO IT.
YOU’LL SHOCK
THE ENTIRE SCHOOL.
IT’LL BLOW
THEIR MINDS.
OKAY, THANKS...
CHIYU.
♪
ALL RIGHT. SEE YA.
( gasps )
HEY. MY MOM’S
NOT HERE TODAY.
NO! STOP!
THIS IS WRONG!
Kuroyukihime:
MIND IF I JOIN?
AAH!
SO, HARUYUKI.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE THREE
REACH A NEW LEVEL TOGETHER?
AAH!
( panting )
( sobs )
I’M SO GONNA BURN IN HELL.
I’M SO ASHAMED.
OH, I’M PATHETIC.
IF I HADN’T CABLE-LINKED
WITH CHIYU,
I NEVER WOULD’VE
HAD THAT DREAM!
Kuroyukihime:
GOOD MORNING,
YOUNG MAN.
AAH!
INTERESTING.
THIS HOW YOU
ALWAYS GREET
PEOPLE?
NO! OF COURSE NOT!
G-GOOD MORNING.
HOW ARE YOU?!
MM...
LISTEN...
BY THE WAY...
ABOUT YESTERDAY...
I APOLOGIZE.
I BEHAVED
IMMATURELY.
AAH! NO!
I’M THE ONE
WHO’S SORRY.
I DIDN’T MEAN
TO HAVE THAT DREAM.
WHAT DREAM?
NOTHING!
NOT THE DREAM!
I MEANT, FOR LEAVING
WITHOUT SAYING GOODBYE.
THAT WAS RUDE.
( chuckles )
I DON’T BLAME YOU.
AFTER ALL,
FIRST I ACCUSED
YOUR BEST FRIEND.
AND THEN I TASKED YOU
WITH A CHALLENGE THAT
WAS SURELY IMPOSSIBLE:
GETTING HER
TO CABLE-LINK
WITH YOU.
UH, ACTUALLY...
I GOT HER TO DO IT.
DO WHAT?
WE CABLE-LINKED.
WHERE WAS THIS?
IT WAS...
AT HER HOUSE.
IN WHICH ROOM?
WELL, WE WERE IN HER...
BEDROOM.
OH?
I WAS ABLE TO HACK IN
AND CHECK HER MEMORY
FOR ANY EVIDENCE--
AND HOW LONG
WAS THIS CABLE?
UH...
THIRTY CENTIMETERS...
OR SO.
HMM!
( gasping, panting )
( school bell chiming )
Haru voice over: WHY DID SHE
JUST STORM OFF LIKE THAT?
( sighs )
I NEED TO TALK TO HER.
I HAVE TO TELL HER
WHAT I FOUND OUT.
HELLO!
AAH!
SO, YOU’RE HARUYUKI ARITA
FROM CLASS 1-C, AREN’T YOU?
WE’RE WITH
UMESATO TIMES.
THE GOSSIP COLUMN
FOR THE SCHOOL PAPER.
WE WRITE THAT!
OKAY,
FIRST QUESTION:
ARE THE
RUMORS TRUE?
ARE YOU
REALLY DATING
KUROYUKIHIME?
AAH!
THAT’S A LIE!
THAT’S
TOTALLY FALSE!
BUT ACCORDING
TO OUR SOURCES,
YOU’VE CABLE-LINKED
WITH HER TWICE IN
THE STUDENT LOUNGE.
AND THEN ONE MORE TIME
OUTSIDE OF SCHOOL
AT A NEARBY
COFFEE SHOP!
YEAH. I...WAS JUST HELPING...
HER FIX HER NEURO-LINKER...
IT’S NOTHING MORE
INTERESTING THAN THAT.
AND THEN SHE TOOK ME
TO A COFFEE SHOP
TO SAY THANK YOU.
THAT’S IT!
LOOK...YOU CAN TELL
SHE DOESN’T LIKE ME
BY THE WAY SHE ACTS
WHENEVER WE’RE TOGETHER.
I MEAN, BY THE END
OF ALL OUR CONVERSATIONS,
SHE’S ALWAYS
IN A BAD MOOD.
REALLY?
YEAH, SHE WENT AND STORMED OFF
AGAIN THIS MORNING.
IT’S...WEIRD.
EVERY TIME I BRING UP
CHIYU’S NAME, SHE JUST--
CHIYURI
KURASHIMA?
OH, RIGHT,
THAT GIRL.
THOSE TWO GOT INTO
IT BY THE SCHOOL
GATES YESTERDAY.
SO...
ARE WE DONE HERE?
YEAH,
NOT QUITE.
WE THOUGHT THE
WHOLE THING
WAS BOGUS.
BUT NOW, I’M
NOT SO SURE
ABOUT THAT.
HEY, ARITA.
I THINK YOU’RE WRONG
ABOUT KUROYUKIHIME.
SHE MIGHT
LIKE YOU
FOR REAL.
AAH!
I MEAN,
COME ON.
SHE GETS MAD EACH
TIME YOU MENTION
ANOTHER GIRL’S NAME?
THE ONLY REASON
FOR THAT...
Both: IS BECAUSE
SHE’S JEALOUS!
( Haru gasps )
CAN’T BE...
School Reporters:
SHE’S JEALOUS!
THERE’S NO WAY!
IT’S A LIE!
IT’S GOTTA BE!
THERE’S NO WAY!
IT JUST CAN’T!
I DON’T GET IT.
COME ON,
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO ME?!
YOU’VE GOT EVERYTHING
YOU COULD EVER WANT.
THE LOOKS, GRADES, POPULARITY.
ALL OF IT!
THERE’S NOW WAY YOU’D GO
FOR SOMEONE LIKE ME!
I’M NOT GONNA BELIEVE IT.
I’M NOT GONNA GET MY HOPES UP
JUST TO HAVE YOU CRUSH THEM.
DAMN IT.
WHY’D YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE ME?
( background chatter )
HEY...
WHY DON’T WE CHAT
WHILE WE WALK?
SURE...
Kuroyukihime:LISTEN.
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THIS MORNING.
I DON’T KNOW
WHAT CAME OVER ME.
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
I FOUND A CONNECTION
BETWEEN CHIYURI
AND CYAN PILE.
HUH? REALLY?
YOU DID?
THEN LET’S CONTINUE
THIS CONVERSATION
VIA CABLE-LINK.
WE DON’T WANT ANYONE
EAVESDROPPING ON THE
IMPORTANT DETAILS, DO WE?
OH...I HAD TO REPLACE
MY PREVIOUS CABLE,
IT JUST SUDDENLY
STOPPED WORKING.
ALL THE STORE HAD
WAS THIS SHORT ONE.
Haru:
CHIYURI’S NOT
CYAN PILE.
SHE’S BEEN HACKED.
SOMEONE SENT A VIRUS
TO HER NEURO-LINKER
AND CREATED
A BACK DOOR
THEY COULD ACCESS.
( Kuroyukihime gasps )
Haru: THAT’S WHY THEY’RE ABLE
TO LOG ONTO THE SCHOOL’S NET
AND USE HER COORDINATES
ON CAMPUS TO CHALLENGE YOU.
Kuroyukihime:
WHAT’S THE MATTER?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU’RE ACTING STRANGE.
Haru: I’M FINE.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
Kuroyukihime:
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
AT SCHOOL TODAY?
Haru: I SAID
DON’T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
LET’S TALK ABOUT
WHAT’S IMPORTANT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY PROOF
OF THIS HACK?
NO. I FIGURED THAT
WHOEVER IT WAS WOULD
NOTICE IF I DID ANYTHING.
SO I LET IT BE.
Kuroyukihime:
THAT’S A LOGICAL RESPONSE,
BUT IT MAKES IT
VERY HARD TO BELIEVE.
REMEMBER, BRAIN BURST
IS CONSIDERED AN
UN-HACKABLE PROGRAM.
CONNECTING TO ITS MATCHING
SERVER THROUGH A BACKDOOR
IS UNHEARD OF. EVEN BY ME.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT I’VE JUST
MADE ALL THIS UP?
SOME ELABORATE LIE
SO I COULD SWITCH SIDES?
THAT’S NOT WHAT I MEANT!
Haru: WELL, IF YOU
DON’T BELIEVE ME,
IT’S NOT REALLY ABOUT
THE EVIDENCE ANYMORE.
LOOK, IT’S UP TO YOU
WHETHER YOU WANT TO
TRUST ME OR NOT.
Kuroyukihime:
IS THAT HOW
YOU TRULY FEEL?
JUST DO WHATEVER
YOU WANT.
I MEAN,
LET’S BE HONEST.
I’M NOTHING MORE
THAN A PAWN.
A TOOL YOU CAN TOSS
ASIDE WHEN YOU’RE
DONE USING IT.
WHY WOULD YOU
SAY THAT?
YOU’RE MAD AT ME,
AREN’T YOU?
LISTEN, THE WAY I
BEHAVED WAS WRONG.
AND I ADMIT THAT.
I’M SORRY!
IT’S JUST...
THERE ARE TIMES WHEN...
WHEN I CAN’T ALWAYS
CONTROL MY EMOTIONS.
AND IT SEEMS, ESPECIALLY
WHEN IT COMES TO YOU
AND KURASHIMA, I JUST...
WHAT I’M TRYING
TO SAY IS...
OKAY,
THAT’S ENOUGH.
HUH?
THIS ISN’T JUST
PAINFUL TO WATCH.
IT’S KIND OF PATHETIC.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
LET ME GUESS.
YOU HATE YOURSELF,
DON’T YOU?
Haru: YOU’RE ONE OF THOSE
GIRLS WHO’S PERFECT AT
EVERYTHING SHE DOES,
AND NOW YOU HATE
YOURSELF FOR IT.
THAT’S WHY
YOU’RE DOING THIS.
DEMEANING YOURSELF
BY PRETENDING TO LIKE
SOMEONE LIKE ME.
I GET IT, OKAY?
BUT JUST DROP THE ACT.
YOU DON’T NEED TO DO THIS.
I’LL DO WHATEVER
YOU WANT ANYWAY.
I DON’T NEED YOUR THANKS,
OR EVEN THE PRETENSE
THAT YOU LIKE ME.
JUST TELL ME WHAT TO
DO, AND TOSS ME ASIDE
WHEN YOU’RE DONE.
THAT’S THE WAY IT WORKS
BETWEEN PEOPLE LIKE
YOU AND ME.
THAT’S HOW YOU
SHOULD TREAT ME,
AND YOU KNOW IT!
( sobs )
( slapping noise )
( gasps )
YOU IDIOT!
( confused noises )
( crying )
Kuroyukihime:
HOW COULD YOU BE...
SO INCREDIBLY STUPID?!
( car tires screeching )
( both gasping )
Both:
BURST LINK!
OH!
Haru:
MAN, THAT WAS CLOSE!
A SPLIT SECOND
LATER, AND...
BUT HOLD ON. WE’VE
ONLY ACCELERATED TIME,
NOT STOPPED IT.
AT SOME POINT,
WE’LL HAVE TO BURST OUT...
THEY SAY A.I. CONTROLLED
CARS ARE FOOLPROOF.
THERE’S NO WAY TO GET
INTO AN ACCIDENT WITH
ONE OF THESE THINGS.
SO, THEN...
WAS THIS ON PURPOSE?
( gasps )
THAT’S...ARAYA!
DOES THIS MEAN
THAT HE’S CYAN PILE?
Kuroyukihime:
NO. HE JUST
WANTS REVENGE.
I BLAME
MYSELF.
I SHOULD HAVE
BEEN MORE CAUTIOUS
AND SEEN THIS COMING.
IF YOU’RE DEAD SET
ON ATTACKING SOMEBODY,
YOU DON’T NEED
ACCELERATION POWERS.
AS WE CAN SEE, A KNIFE
OR A CAR WILL DO FINE.
I SUPPOSE I HAD
THIS COMING.
MY PUNISHMENT FOR TOYING
WITH THE LIVES OF OTHERS,
WITHOUT EVER CARING
HOW THAT MAY AFFECT THEM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HARUYUKI,
FORGIVE ME.
I’M THE PERSON
WHO HAS CAUSED
ALL THIS.
BUT I PROMISE TO NEVER
LET YOU GET HURT.
I’LL PROTECT YOU
AT ALL COSTS.
UM, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THERE’S AN ASPECT
OF BRAIN BURST THAT I
HAVE YET TO TELL YOU ABOUT:
THE ULTIMATE AND FINAL
ACCELERATION POWER.
NO! WHATEVER IT IS,
YOU CAN NEVER USE IT!
IF A POWER LIKE THAT
EXISTS, THEN LET ME USE IT.
I’M YOUR PAWN, THAT’S WHAT
I’M SUPPOSED TO DO.
I HAVE TO PROTECT YOU
AT ALL COSTS!
YOU CAN’T.
THE ONLY ONES WHO
CAN USE THIS POWER
ARE THE PLAYERS WHO
HAVE REACHED LEVEL 9.
AND YOU LOSE 99%
OF YOUR POINTS
WHEN YOU DO.
BUT REGARDLESS
OF ALL THAT,
I’M YOUR GUARDIAN.
I HAVE TO
PROTECT YOU.
( sobs )
YEAH, BUT--
THERE’S NO REASON
TO CRY.
I HAVE TO SAY...
AT LEAST THERE’S
ONE POSITIVE THING
COMING FROM ALL THIS.
LIKE WHAT?
IN A DIRE MOMENT
LIKE THIS...
I THINK YOU MIGHT
ACTUALLY BELIEVE
MY FINAL WORDS.
AT LEAST I HOPE SO.
HARUYUKI... PLEASE KNOW
THAT I LOVE YOU.
( gasps )
I’VE NEVER
FELT THIS WAY
ABOUT ANYONE.
AND IT’S BEEN
VERY CONFUSING
FOR ME.
I’M CONSTANTLY
THINKING ABOUT YOU...
AND THESE THOUGHTS I HAVE
MAKE ME BOTH HAPPY AND SAD.
I GUESS THAT’S JUST WHAT
BEING IN LOVE DOES TO YOU.
BUT WHY ME? I MEAN,
OF ALL THE PEOPLE...
WHY WOULD YOU EVER
CHOOSE ME?
WELL, THINK BACK.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE
FIRST TIME YOU AND I MADE
CONTACT WITH EACH OTHER?
YES, OF COURSE.
Kuroyukihime: IN ORDER
TO BEAT YOU AT THAT GAME
AND GET THE HIGHEST SCORE,
I HAD TO ACCELERATE.
HUH?
I WANTED TO
IMPRESS YOU,
SO I COULD PERSUADE
YOU MORE EASILY.
I’VE BEEN A BURST-LINKER
FOR OVER SIX YEARS NOW.
AND IN MY QUEST FOR SPEED
AND POWER, I’VE SLAUGHTERED
THOUSANDS OF ENEMIES...
AND ALONG THE WAY,
EVEN A FEW OF MY FRIENDS.
BUT EVEN SOMEONE AS HIGHLY
RANKED AS ME COULD COME
NOWHERE NEAR YOUR HIGH SCORE.
YOU’RE THE FASTEST
THERE IS, NO ONE
IS BETTER. NO ONE.
AND I KNOW THAT SOMEDAY,
THE REST OF THE ACCELERATED
WORLD WILL KNOW THIS AS WELL,
THAT YOU ARE THE
FASTEST LINKER
TO EVER EXIST.
YOU WILL DEFEAT THE KINGS,
RISE UP TO THE NEXT LEVEL,
AND DISCOVER THE TRUE
MEANING OF BRAIN BURST.
AND BY DOING THAT, YOU WILL
UNLOCK THE TRUE POTENTIAL
THAT LIES DEEP WITHIN
OUR MINDS AND SOULS.
WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU
PLAYING THAT GAME,
MY BODY TREMBLED
WITH EXCITEMENT.
WATCHING SOMEONE BE
SO FAST AND MAGNIFICENT,
AND YET...
IN THE REAL WORLD,
YOU’RE SO PAINFULLY FRAGILE.
WHEN I FINALLY
REALIZED THIS,
IT HURT MY HEART
SO MUCH IT NEARLY
TORE ME APART.
( sobs )
I WANT TO BOW
BEFORE YOU LIKE
I WOULD A KING...
WHICH YOU WILL BECOME.
BUT I ALSO WANT TO
HOLD AND PROTECT YOU.
ALL OF THESE CONTRADICTORY
FEELINGS FINALLY WELLED
UP INSIDE ME...
AND I REALLY
FELL FOR YOU.
BUT I ONLY
FULLY REALIZED
THIS YESTERDAY.
YESTERDAY?
WHEN YOU TOLD ME ABOUT
CABLE-LINKING WITH
KURASHIMA.
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN MY LIFE, I WAS
JEALOUS OF SOMEONE.
I WISH I’D REALIZED
THIS SOONER.
BUT STILL, I HAVE BEEN
AFFORDED THIS MOMENT.
MY CHANCE TO DECLARE
MY LOVE FOR YOU.
I HAD HOPED THAT I WOULD
BE ABLE TO TELL YOU THIS
IN THE REAL WORLD.
BUT NOW, MY TIME IS UP.
( sobs )
WORK HARD.
GET STRONGER
AND FASTER.
CLIMB YOUR WAY
TO THE TOP.
AND SEE THE WORLD
FROM THERE
IN MY PLACE.
NO, DON’T!
YOU CAN’T
LEAVE ME LIKE THIS.
I’M THE ONE WHO’S
SUPPOSED TO PROTECT YOU!
BUT...
I HAVEN’T.
I HAVEN’T DONE...
ANYTHING FOR YOU.
( gasps )
IT’S OKAY.
I’M SURE WE’LL
MEET AGAIN SOMEDAY.
NO! PLEASE DON’T
DO THIS! PLEASE!
STOP!
PHYSICAL
FULL BURST!
( grunting )
( gasps )
IMPOSSIBLE...
HER BODY.
IT’S MOVING!
Kuroyukihime:
THERE’S A THEORY
THAT SUGGESTS
THAT ONE’S HEARTBEAT IS
THE BASE CLOCK FOR THE SPEED
OF HUMAN THOUGHT PROCESS.
WHY DOES TIME SEEM TO SLOW DOWN
TO A CRAWL FOR SOMEONE LIKE
A RACECAR DRIVER?
OR HOW CAN A MINUTE FEEL LIKE
AN ETERNITY FOR TWO LOVERS WHEN
THEY’RE IN EACH OTHER’S ARMS?
IT’S BECAUSE WHEN THE HUMAN
HEART RATE INCREASES, SO DOES
OUR CAPACITY TO PROCESS DATA.
BRAIN BURST
UTILIZES THIS THEORY.
BY ACCESSING THE NEURO-LINKER,
IT SPEEDS UP YOUR HEART RATE-
THE BASE CLOCK-
A THOUSAND TIMES, AND IN
RETURN, IT ACCELERATES
YOUR THOUGHT PROCESS.
ACCESSING THIS ILLICIT POWER
WITHIN YOUR OWN BODY
IS CALLED...
PHYSICAL FULL BURST.
HARUYUKI... WHENEVER I’M
WITH YOU, MY HEART IS
ALWAYS RACING NONSTOP.
EVEN WITHOUT THE ASSISTANCE
OF A NEURO-LINKER
OR BRAIN BURST,
I CONSTANTLY FELT
LIKE I WAS ACCELERATING
AROUND YOU.
THAT’S WHY I CAN DIE
WITH A SMILE.
BECAUSE IN A SHORT TIME,
YOU HAVE GIVEN ME AN ETERNITY.
( sobbing )
( loud crash )
Man: WHAT HAPPENED?!
Woman: SOMEBODY GET HELP!
( grunting )
( scattered crowd chatter )
Woman:
CAME OUT
OF NOWHERE.
Man:
SHE OKAY?
( gasps )
Woman:
OH!
( crowd murmuring )
Haru ( sobbing ):
NO!
( sobbing )
Haru:
HER SCHOOL JOURNAL...
( gasps )
IT’S MY FAULT.
IT’S ALL MY FAULT...
( bawling )
Doctor: WE’VE
MANAGED TO STOP
THE BLEEDING.
THE SYNTHETIC PROTEIN
MICRO-MACHINES ARE
CURRENTLY WORKING FULL TIME
IN ORDER TO REPAIR
THE AFFECTED TISSUE.
BUT THERE’S A LOT
OF INTERNAL DAMAGE,
AND THE POTENTIAL FOR
HER TO GO INTO SHOCK
AT ANY MOMENT IS HIGH.
JUST KNOW THAT
THE NEXT 12 HOURS
WILL BE VERY CRITICAL.
TWELVE HOURS.
Nurse: YOU REALLY SHOULD
GO HOME AND REST.
WE’VE ALREADY CONTACTED
HER FAMILY.
SOMEONE WILL
COME BY TOMORROW.
BUT THEN
IT MAY BE
TOO LATE.
I CAN’T JUST
LEAVE HER ALONE
WHEN SHE’S
IN THERE FIGHTING
FOR HER LIFE.
I’M STAYING.
ALL RIGHT,
THEN.
IF YOU’RE GOING
TO STAY, I’LL
GET YOU A BLANKET.
TRY TO GET SOME
REST IF YOU CAN.
( gasps )
WAIT! W-WHAT ABOUT
HER NEURO-LINKER?
YOU DON’T KNOW
IF SHE STILL HAS
IT ON HER, DO YOU?
YES. THAT’S HOW
WE’RE MONITORING
HER BRAINWAVES.
AND IS THAT LIKE
A STAND-ALONE
MACHINE,
OR DO YOU HAVE IT
LINKED INTO SOME
OTHER NETWORK?
WELL, YES, IT CONNECTS
HER TO THE NET HERE
AT THE HOSPITAL.
BUT THAT MEANS...
BURST LINK!
( grunts )
( gasps )
OH, NO!
WHEN SHE USED
PHYSICAL FULL BURST,
SHE LOST 99%
OF HER POINTS.
IF SOMEONE TRIES
TO ATTACK HER HERE...
CALM DOWN.
THE CHANCES OF RUNNING
INTO A LINKER AT A HOSPITAL
HAVE GOT TO BE PRETTY SLIM.
( gasps )
BUT...WHAT ABOUT CYAN PILE?
IF HE SHOWS UP, IT’S OVER!
HER DREAMS...
ALL OF IT, FINISHED!
NO. I WON’T LET THAT HAPPEN.
I’LL PROTECT YOU.
I WON’T LET THIS BE THE END.
THERE’S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TELL HER.
WHICH MEANS, IT’S MY TURN
TO STEP UP.
IF I WANT TO SEE HER AGAIN,
I’VE GOTTA FIGHT.
IF SOMEONE DOES
BURST LINK HERE,
THEN CHANCES ARE
IT’LL BE CYAN PILE.
I’LL ONLY HAVE A MOMENT
TO REACT...
BEFORE THEY CHALLENGE HER.
( gasps )
NO WAY!
KUROYUKIHIME WAS IN
AN ACCIDENT?
HARU...
Woman on P.A.:
GOOD MORNING.
WE ARE ABOUT TO BEGIN
REGULAR VISITING HOURS.
IF YOU ARE HERE AS A VISITOR,
PLEASE GO TO COUNTERS
1 THROUGH 4.
ALL RIGHT, IT’S STARTING
TO GET BUSY.
PLEASE...
HURRY UP AND GET WELL.
SO I CAN TELL YOU
MY TRUE FEELINGS.
( gasps )
WHAT? TAKU?
IS HE HERE VISITING?
TAKU!
WAIT...
WHY IS HE HERE?
I’M SURE OUR SCHOOL KNOWS
ABOUT THE ACCIDENT BY NOW,
BUT HE DOESN’T GO
TO OUR SCHOOL.
IS HE HERE WITH CHIYU?
NO.
HE’S BY HIMSELF.
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS
DOESN’T FEEL RIGHT.
WHAT MADE ME THINK THAT
CYAN PILE WENT TO OUR SCHOOL
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
IT’S BECAUSE THEY INSTALLED
A BACKDOOR PROGRAM IN CHIYU
TO MAKE IT SEEM
LIKE THEY WERE THERE.
BUT WHO WOULD HAVE
THAT ACCESS?
WHO’S THE ONLY ONE
WHO CABLE-LINKS WITH CHIYU?
TAKU!
HUH?
( chuckles )
( gasps )
Both:
BURST LINK!
( grunts )
WHY, TAKU?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?!
DON’T LET ME BE TOO LATE!
♪
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE, "AVIATION."
THE YOUNG MAN FINALLY
BEGINS TO SHINE.
HE SPREADS HIS SILVER WINGS
AND TAKES TO THE SKIES.