Niko:YELLOW RADIO.
HUH?
WHAT? WHY IS THE YELLOW
KING HERE?
WAIT. HE’S A KING?!
IF HE’S THE LEADER
OF THE YELLOW LEGION,
THEN HE’S A LEVEL NINE
BURST LINKER!
NOW I GET IT, YA BASTARD!
YOU SET THIS UP,
YELLOW RADIO!
THIS WAS ALL YOU!
WHAT’S THIS?
WHY, IF IT
ISN’T THE RED KING.
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
DON’T PLAY ALL INNOCENT
WITH ME.
YOU WERE LYING IN WAIT
FOR US.
SHE’S RIGHT.
ONE SECOND IN REAL TIME
IS 17 MINUTES HERE.
THERE’S NO WAY YOU CAN
RUN INTO OTHER PLAYERS
LIKE THIS
UNLESS YOU’VE PLANNED IT
AHEAD OF TIME.
THERE MUST BE SOME
MISUNDERSTANDING.
I’M ONLY HERE
BECAUSE ONE OF YOUR MEMBERS
HAS BEEN
ATTACKING MY SUBORDINATES,
STRIPPING THEM
OF ALL THEIR POINTS,
CLEARLY VIOLATING
THE NON-AGGRESSION TREATY.
SOMEONE MUST
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
YELLOW KING MUST HAVE
KEPT THE ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE
HIDDEN AWAY ALL THIS TIME!
( metal clashing )
THEN HE GAVE IT
TO CHERRY ROOK
TO LURE OUT NIKO...
SO HE COULD
AMBUSH SCARLET RAIN!
DO I NEED TO REMIND YOU
OF WHAT THE TREATY STATES?
"IN THE EVENT THAT A LEGION
MEMBER HAS THEIR PROGRAM
FORCIBLY UNINSTALLED
"DUE TO AN ATTACK THAT
IS A DIRECT VIOLATION
OF THE TREATY,
"THAT LEGION IS THEN GIVEN
THE POWER TO CHOOSE ANY PLAYER
FROM THE OFFENDING LEGION
AND ENSURE THAT THEY
MEET THE EXACT SAME FATE."
WHAT A COINCIDENCE...
THE PERSON WE CHOSE
ALSO HAPPENS TO BE THE HEAD
OF THE RED LEGION,
SCARLET RAIN.
THIS IS JUST A COLD-BLOODED
HUNT TO TAKE A KING’S HEAD.
AND THE ONLY REASON
HE’S DOING THIS...
IS SO HE CAN REACH LEVEL 10!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Niko: SO YOU’RE JUST
FOLLOWING THE RULES,
IS THAT IT, RADIO?
I’M GLAD TO SEE
YOU UNDERSTAND.
YEAH, BUT THE TREATY
ALSO STATES THIS:
"YOU CAN CHOOSE ANYONE
YOU WISH FOR REVENGE
"EXCEPT IN AN INSTANCE
WHERE THE LEGION MASTER
THEMSELVES
HAS PUNISHED THE OFFENDING
PLAYER BY REMOVING ALL
THEIR POINTS."
VERY TRUE.
BUT THERE’S A LITTLE RUMOR
FLOATING AROUND
THAT YOU TRIED TO DO THAT
AND FAILED SPECTACULARLY.
( grunts )
OF COURSE, YOU’RE
FREE TO TRY AGAIN.
BUT WHEN WILL THE CULPRIT
WE SPEAK OF APPEAR?
AND WHEN WILL YOU
ACTUALLY PUNISH HIM?
IF YOU CAN’T DO IT IMMEDIATELY,
I’M AFRAID WE’LL HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE’LL HAVE TO MAKE DUE
WITH YOU.
WE’RE WAY OUTNUMBERED.
LET’S LOG OUT FOR NOW.
WE CAN GO AFTER CHROME
DISASTER ANOTHER TIME.
WE CAN’T.
HUH?
THE UNLIMITED NEUTRAL FIELD
DOESN’T ALLOW PLAYERS
TO DO INSTANT LOG-OUTS.
( gasps )
SHE’S RIGHT, HARU.
IF YOU WANT TO LOG OUT,
YOU HAVE TO GO TO SPECIFIED
LEAVE POINTS WHICH ARE SCATTERED
THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE FIELD.
Taku: THAT’S
HOW IT WORKS HERE.
Haru: OKAY, FINE.
LET’S GO TO A LEAVE
POINT, THEN.
EXCEPT THE CLOSEST ONES
ARE IKEBUKURO STATION
OR SUNSHINE CITY.
MEANING EITHER WAY,
WE CAN’T AVOID A DIRECT
CONFRONTATION.
( gasps )
BUT, WE STILL HAVE A CHANCE
AT WINNING THIS GAME.
( whimpers )
WHAT’S THAT?
SEE, THE CREW THAT BASTARD
PUT TOGETHER WAS ONLY
TO HUNT ME DOWN.
HE DIDN’T EXPECT ME
TO BRING HELP.
HOWEVER NOW,
THERE’S ONE MORE KING
HE HAS TO DEAL WITH.
( gasps )
Yellow Radio:
IT’S BEEN QUITE A WHILE,
BLACK LOTUS.
I’D APPRECIATE IF YOU’D
KINDLY STEP ASIDE ON THIS ONE
AND ENJOY THE SHOW
THAT’S ABOUT TO UNFOLD.
YOU MUST BE JOKING,
YELLOW RADIO.
WHY SHOULD I BOTHER
GOING ALONG WITH ONE
OF YOUR SILLY LITTLE GAMES?
MY GOODNESS.
SO REBELLIOUS.
AND AFTER I’D GONE TO ALL
THE TROUBLE OF PREPARING
THIS SPECIAL GIFT FOR YOU.
( Haru whimpers )
WHAT IS THAT?
Niko: IT’S THE FIRST
RED KING, RED RIDER.
WHAT?
YOU MEAN THAT’S HIM?
( Kuroyukihime whimpering )
( gasps )
Red Rider: MY FELLOW KINGS,
I ASK YOU AGAIN--
IS THIS REALLY WHAT WE WANT?
BETRAYING
AND KILLING EACH OTHER?
ALL FOR SOME STUPID GOAL?
IT’S NOT RIGHT.
YES, WE LEAD LEGIONS
AND FIGHT ONE ANOTHER,
BUT THAT’S BECAUSE WE
CONSIDER EACH OTHER
TO BE WORTHY RIVALS,
NOT ENEMIES.
LOTUS, I HAVE A GREAT DEAL
OF RESPECT FOR THE WAY YOU
FIGHT.
I BET IF WE WERE TO MEET
IN THE REAL WORLD,
WE’D BE FRIENDS.
IN FACT, I’D LIKE THAT.
THAT’S WHY I HAVE NO DESIRE
TO FIGHT YOU IN A SUDDEN-DEATH
DUEL.
COME ON, I KNOW YOU
FEEL THE SAME.
Purple Thorn: ENOUGH, RIDER.
ARE YOU FLIRTING WITH THAT WOMAN
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME?
WHOA. EASY THERE, BABE.
I DIDN’T MEAN IT LIKE THAT.
SORRY.
Kuroyukihime: YOU’RE RIGHT.
HUH?
I FEEL THE SAME WAY, RIDER.
I LIKE YOU, TOO.
I MEAN, I RESPECT YOU
AS A KING.
OF ALL PEOPLE, LOTUS,
I KNEW YOU’D UNDERSTAND.
UH...
AH.
MY APOLOGIES.
LET’S TRY THIS INSTEAD.
( both grunting )
YOU LITTLE BITCH!
IT’S OKAY.
DON’T GET MAD.
IT’S JUST HER WAY
OF SHAKING HANDS.
DEATH BY EMBRACING.
( gasps )
NO!
Purple Thorn: NO!
( laughs )
THE GOOD OLD TIMES.
( Haru whimpers )
Kuroyukihime: STOP IT.
( grunts )
STOP IT. STOP IT.
STOP IT!
SENPAI?!
HARUYUKI?
( whimpering )
NO. DON’T LOOK AT ME.
( gasps )
SENPAI!
WHAT’S WRONG?!
WHAT HAPPENED?!
ZERO FILL.
WHAT?
LOTUS...
I HAD NO IDEA.
( Yellow Radio laughing )
HUH?
Yellow Lotus:
I THOUGHT THAT BETRAYAL MIGHT
STILL WEIGH HEAVY ON HER.
AND TO THINK SOMEONE
AS WEAK AS HER WAS AIMING
FOR LEVEL 10.
WHAT A JOKE!
( laughs )
PREPARE TO ATTACK!
( breathing heavily )
FINE. BRING IT ON!
ENHANCED!
Taku: NO, DON’T DO IT!
IF YOU ACTIVATE YOUR
WEAPONRY RIGHT NOW,
YOU’LL BE STUCK HERE.
OUR BEST OPTION IS TO RETREAT
AND HEAD FOR THE SUNSHINE CITY
LEAVE POINT.
( grunts )
HARU, I’LL ACT AS COVER.
YOU TAKE CARE OF OUR MASTER.
WHAT?! THAT’S INSANE.
YOU CAN’T!
LOOK, IF THEY DEFEAT THE RED
KING, THEN THEY’LL DEFINITELY
GO AFTER OUR MASTER NEXT.
NO MATTER WHAT,
WE CAN’T LET THAT HAPPEN!
( grunts )
I GOT YA.
GET THEM!
LET’S GO!
RIGHT!
( grunting )
( screams )
( yells )
( groaning )
MAN!
WHAT THE HELL?!
HARU! BE CAREFUL...
OUR PAIN SENSITIVITY
IS DOUBLED WHILE WE’RE IN HERE.
( both gasp )
( yelling )
( Niko and Taku yell )
TAKU! NIKO!
HARU, RUN!
OKAY!
ALMOST THERE.
I JUST GOT TO GET
TO THE CRATER’S EDGE.
IF I CAN GET THERE,
I CAN GRAB SENPAI
AND NIKO AND FLY OFF!
( laughing )
OH, NO YOU DON’T.
SILLY GO ROUND!
( gasps )
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
( merry-go-round
music playing )
THE FIELD...
IT’S SPINNING.
IT’S NOT.
IT ONLY LOOKS THAT WAY.
YOU’VE JUST GOT
TO CLOSE YOUR EYES AND RUN.
GET DOWN!
( grunts )
( groaning )
( gasps )
TAKU!
( groans )
IT’S OKAY, HARU.
THIS IS THE LEAST I CAN DO
TO MAKE UP FOR EVERYTHING
I’VE DONE.
SHUT UP!
STOP SAYING THAT!
I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
YOU OWE ME NOTHING!
( screaming )
TAKU!
I TAKE BACK THAT COMMENT
ABOUT YOU JUST BEING BRAINY,
CYAN PILE.
HANG IN THERE.
RADIO’S SPECIAL MOVE
WILL BE OVER IN 30 SECONDS.
STAY STRONG AND LAST IT OUT.
( groaning )
Green Avatar: ( laughs )
I HEARD YOU WERE ONE
TOUGH DUDE, CYAN PILE.
BUT IT SEEMS THAT
WAS NOTHING MORE THAN TALK.
( groaning )
REMEMBER THIS BEFORE YOU DIE:
THE NAME OF THE GUY
WHO FINISHED YOU IS SAXE--
I DON’T CARE
ABOUT YOUR STUPID NAME!
LIGHTNING CYAN SPIKE!
( yells )
TAKU!
( grunts )
HARU.
THE REST IS UP TO YOU.
NOW GO!
SPLASH STINGER!
( yells )
TAKU, YOU’RE AMAZING.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW PROUD I AM
TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
( yelling )
( all gasping )
TAKU, SENPAI,
COME ON.
WHAT’S GOING ON?
WHY WON’T YOU WAKE UP?!
IT’S NO USE, SILVER CROW.
( whimpers )
SHE’S IN ZERO-FILL
STATE RIGHT NOW.
THE SIGNAL HER SOUL GENERATES
AND TRANSMITS TO HER AVATAR
HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN
AND ZEROED OUT.
WHEN A BURST LINKER
LOSES THEIR WILL TO FIGHT,
THEY CAN’T
CONTROL THEIR DUEL AVATAR.
IF YOU’RE NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO FACE YOUR OWN EMOTIONAL
SCARS,
THEN YOU WON’T EVEN
HAVE THE STRENGTH TO STAND UP.
THAT’S THE KIND OF GAME
BRAIN BURST IS.
Haru: HER EMOTIONAL SCARS?
SILVER CROW, TAKE LOTUS
AND GET OUT OF HERE.
( whimpers )
I’M SORRY.
I KNOW CYAN PILE SACRIFICED
HIMSELF JUST TO BUY US TIME,
BUT...
RUNNING AWAY FROM A FIGHT
HAS NEVER REALLY BEEN MY STYLE.
ME, NEITHER!
( grunts )
I WON’T GO.
I HATE THE IDEA OF RUNNING AWAY
AND LEAVING FRIENDS BEHIND!
DID YOU SAY "FRIENDS"?
YOU’VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
YOU REALLY
ARE A COMPLETE IDIOT.
SUIT YOURSELF.
YELLOW RADIO, I’M GUESSING
YOU’VE PRETTY MUCH EXHAUSTED
YOUR SPECIAL MOVE GAUGE,
WHICH MEANS IT’S MY TURN
TO PUT ON A SHOW.
AND REMEMBER...
IF I DESTROY YOU,
THEN YOU WILL BE BANISHED
FROM HERE FOREVER!
( gasps )
LET’S GO.
ENHANCED ARMAMENT!
ALL RIGHT, SILVER CROW,
TAKE CARE OF THE CLOSE-RANGE
COMBAT FIGHTERS WHO LIKE
TO CLIMB UP MY ASS.
AND IF THEY DEFEAT ME,
TAKE LOTUS AND FLY TO SAFETY.
GOT IT.
( indistinct murmuring )
Yellow Radio:
WHAT ARE YOU SO SCARED OF?
THAT’S JUST ONE BIG,
IMMOVABLE FORT.
GET CLOSE ENOUGH,
AND IT’S NOTHING MORE
THAN A HUNK OF IRON.
NOW STOP BEING AFRAID OF IT
AND ATTACK!
( all yelling )
( yells )
GET READY,
YA LITTLE BASTARDS,
’CAUSE YOU’RE ABOUT
TO FIND OUT WHAT IT’S LIKE
TO SUFFER THE WRATH
OF THE RED KING!
( yelling )
( screaming )
( laughing )
THAT’S...AMAZING.
STAY HERE.
GOIN’ SOMEWHERE, PAL?!
MAGNETRON WAVE!
( yells )
( laughing )
YOU METAL COLOR TYPES
ARE TOO EASY.
HUH?
( yelps )
NO, WAIT!
I ONLY HAVE A FEW
SECONDS LEFT
BEFORE MY SPECIAL MOVE ENDS!
( dings )
( screams )
( laughing )
( grunting )
( grunts, yells )
( grunts )
REMEMBER, YOU ARE WEAK
AGAINST PLAYERS
WITH BLUNT ATTACKS.
SO WHEN YOU FACE THEM
AT CLOSE RANGE, YOU HAVE
TO ELUDE THEIR ATTACKS
AND USE THEIR MOMENTUM
AGAINST THEM.
YOU HAVE THE REFLEXES
NEEDED FOR THIS ALREADY.
( grunts )
( yelling )
( laughs )
YOU KNOW, FOR A WIMP,
YOU’RE DOING PRETTY WELL,
SILVER CROW.
THANKS!
( gasps )
DAMN IT.
THEY’VE GOT A JAMMER.
FIND THEM!
IT’S MOST LIKELY
A YELLOW-COLOR LINKER.
( grunts )
GOT IT!
( grunting )
( yells )
ELECTRIC THERAPY!
( screaming )
( laughing )
WHY DON’T YOU JUST STAY DOWN
FOR A LITTLE BIT, KID?
AT LEAST UNTIL WE’RE FINISHED
STRIPPING THE RED KING!
SHIT!
( laughing )
WHAT A PATHETIC
AND UNSEEMLY SIGHT!
THERE’S NOT EVEN A SHRED
OF ROYAL DIGNITY.
I SUPPOSE THAT’S WHAT
YOU’D EXPECT, THOUGH,
FROM AN UPSTART
AND A TRAITOR.
( gasps )
( screaming )
ALL RIGHT!
THIS RED KING
AIN’T NO BIG DEAL AFTER ALL!
YOU GUYS FINISH
STRIPPING HER DOWN
AND THEN DRAG HER OUT OF HERE.
( shouting )
( groaning )
Haru: SENPAI!
SENPAI!
ARE YOU JUST GOING
TO LET THIS HAPPEN?!
LET IT END LIKE THIS?!
IS THIS REALLY THE ENDING
THAT YOU WISHED FOR?!
ANSWER ME!
COME ON, ACCELERATING
AND BRAIN BURST...
DOES IT MEAN THAT
LITTLE TO YOU?!
( screaming )
( gasps )
YOU WANTED NOTHING MORE
THAN TO BE THE FIRST PERSON
TO EVER REACH LEVEL 10!
ARE YOU SO WEAK THAT YOU’RE
WILLING TO ABANDON THIS DREAM
ALL OVER THE MEMORY
OF ONE GUY?!
HOW LONG DO YOU
PLAN TO LIE THERE SLEEPING?!
YOU SWORE TO ME THAT YOU
WOULD MEET EVERY OBSTACLE
FACE-ON...
THAT YOU WOULD TAKE DOWN
EVERY OPPONENT
AND KEEP PUSHING ON
UNTIL YOU WERE THE LAST
ONE STANDING!
BLACK LOTUS, WAKE UP!!!
( gasps )
HMM?
SEN...PAI.
HARUYUKI.
YES!
YOU REALIZE THE WAY YOU PUT IT
MAKES IT SOUND LIKE RIDER AND I
WERE IN LOVE WITH EACH OTHER.
HUH?
BUT I THOUGHT...
YOU’RE COMPLETELY WRONG!
I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
YOU ARE MY FIRST AND ONLY.
NOW, STOP LYING THERE
AND TRY DIGGING ONE
OF YOUR HANDS INTO THE GROUND.
( groans )
HUH?
HUH?!
OH, CRAP!
RIGHT. I JUST
NEEDED TO GROUND IT.
YOU CAN MANAGE THE REST
ON YOUR OWN.
I’LL GO AND HELP OUT
OUR LITTLE RED FRIEND.
( grunts )
( yells )
( screams )
SORRY, BUT GRAPPLING MOVES
REALLY AREN’T THE BEST
TACTICS TO USE ON ME.
HMM?
I HARBOR NO GRUDGE
AGAINST ANY OF YOU.
BUT THAT SAID,
IF ANY ONE OF YOU
TRIES TO FIGHT ME,
I CAN PRETTY MUCH GUARANTEE
THAT AT THE VERY LEAST,
YOU’LL LOSE A LIMB OR TWO.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
IT’LL BE TWICE AS PAINFUL
ON THIS FIELD.
BUT IT’S TOO LATE TO BACK
DOWN NOW, ISN’T IT?
Blue Avatar: TIME OUT!
I’M IN THE MIDDLE
OF CHARGING MY BATTERY!
Haru: LIKE I CARE!
DIDN’T THINK SO!
( gasps )
WHY?! WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS, BLACK LOTUS?
YOU’VE BEEN HIDING ALL THESE
YEARS, SO WHY APPEAR NOW
AND GET IN MY WAY?!
HAVE YOU ALREADY FORGOTTEN
WHAT YOU’VE DONE IN THE PAST?
YOU BETRAYED OUR FRIEND,
RED RIDER,
BY BEHEADING HIM!
OH, THAT POOR MAN.
WHAT DO YOU
SUPPOSE HE’S DOING NOW?
COULD HE BE SITTING SOMEWHERE,
YEARNING FOR THE WORLD
THAT HE CAN NO LONGER RETURN TO?
OR MAYBE HE CURSES THE PERSON
RESPONSIBLE FOR HIS MISERY.
I KNOW THAT’S SOMETHING
I’D NEVER BE ABLE TO FORGET.
IT MIGHT BE EASIER TO TAKE
IF IT HAD BEEN A FAIR FIGHT.
BUT A SNEAKY SURPRISE ATTACK?
DON’T LISTEN TO HIM!
THERE’S A VERY IMPORTANT FACTOR
THAT YOU’RE STILL MISSING,
YELLOW RADIO.
( laughing )
OH, REALLY. WHAT’S THAT?
YOU’RE ASSUMING THAT
TAKING YOUR HEAD
WILL BOTHER ME AS MUCH
AS TAKING RED RIDER’S.
BUT IT WON’T.
AND HERE’S YET ANOTHER THING
THAT YOU HAVE FAILED
TO COMPLETELY COMPREHEND.
EVER SINCE WE’VE FIRST MET,
I’VE HATED YOU!
( grunts )
RAIN, USE YOUR REMAINING AMMO
ON THE ENEMIES AROUND US.
AND CROW,
YOU COVER FOR HER!
HE’S MINE.
( groaning )
DAMN IT.
SHE MAKES IT SOUND SO EASY.
CROW!
TAKE OUT THAT JAMMING SIGNAL!
( gasps )
Haru: ON IT!
( grunts )
NO WAY. NOT THIS TIME!
( yelling )
( screams )
NIKO!
AND...FIRE!
LOTUS!
( grunts )
IT’S SO FAST.
SO THIS IS WHAT A FIGHT
BETWEEN TWO LEVEL-NINE
LINKERS LOOKS LIKE.
WATCH CAREFULLY.
IT’S THE FIRST TIME
IN THE HISTORY
OF ACCELERATED WORLD
THAT TWO LEVEL-NINE PLAYERS
HAVE GONE AT EACH OTHER
IN FULL-OUT BATTLE!
( spectators yelling )
( grunts )
THEY’RE ALMOST THERE.
( gasps )
Niko: EACH OF THEM IS ABOUT
TO HAVE THEIR SPECIAL MOVE GAUGE
AT FULL CHARGE.
THAT’S WHEN
THE REAL BATTLE BEGINS!
( grunts )
Niko: THE SPECIAL MOVE
FROM LOTUS WILL PROBABLY
BE SOME SORT
OF DIRECT ATTACK.
AND I BET RADIO
WILL USE SOME KIND OF ILLUSION.
LOTUS ONLY HAS ONE SHOT.
SHE HAS TO GET TO RADIO
BEFORE HIS SPECIAL MOVE
COMES INTO PLAY.
IT’S THE ONLY CHANCE
SHE HAS.
( breathing heavily )
DEATH BY PIERCING!
FATAL FORTUNE WH--
( groans )
( gasps )
( growls )
♪
( indistinct singing )
♪ IT’S A BURST OF SENSATION ♪
( singing in Japanese )
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE: ABSOLUTION.
A TIME OF JUDGMENT
IS AT HAND.
BUT WILL FAMILIAL BONDS
BE HARDER TO BREAK
THAN ENFORCING JUSTICE?