What? We're moving?
Two weeks from now?
Okay...
What's wrong, Taka...?
You've been acting
weird lately.
We need to talk.
About what?
It's big... But I wanna
tell you tomorrow.
We can meet back here
if that's cool with you.
Yeah, I'm totally
fine with that...
Honestly, There's something
I've been meaning
to tell you too.
Tomorrow, then.
I wanted to tell
him in two days,
I was gonna be moving away.
But...
The next day I waited
until the sun went down...
He never showed up.
So I left...
I ended up leaving without
ever saying goodbye
to my only friend.
Crazy dream.
What's she doing in here?
Huh? What was I
dreaming about again?
[Music]
There Aren't Many
Customers at the Karaoke Box
Has this semester gone by
crazy fast to you guys too,
or is that just me?
Yeah, summer vacation
starts tomorrow... Weird.
As you know, the
Neighbor's Club exists
for one reason only...
And that's to
make friends...
Now, has anyone here
made even one friend?
Anyone have fun-filled
summer plans
with said new friends?
Actually... For me...
I think my rep's worse
now than it was
before I joined.
Me too...
Earlier, I heard some
girls talking about me
and they said, "you know
Sena is totally dating
that blond thug!"
How they could even
believe that much less
repeat it is beyond me.
I should punch
their faces off.
Yeah, that sucks... sorry.
No... You don't have
to apologize
because they're stupid.
What kind of
club activities
have you all been
doing so far?
Have they helped you
make new friends?
Well, let me
think about it...
We played some
video games...
And that's all.
We practiced
role-playing...
With video games.
So... For the most part you've
just been fooling around.
Hey... I have a question...
Have any of you ever
been to one of those...
Karaoke Box things?
Like where you can rent
your own private karaoke room?
Yeah. I've been, too.
What?!
Why are you both
so surprised?
It's hard to imagine you
singing karaoke, that's all.
Whatever! I may not look
like it to you freaks,
but I'll have you know,
I've been to all the
karaoke boxes in the city.
Wow... That seems excessive.
And sad.
Why would you go to every
single one by yourself?
Who said I was by
myself, Jackwagon?!
Karaoke boxes are
obviously places
you go with friends.
-Huh, what?
-Huh?!
Singing karaoke with
your friends is fun. Hello.
Not only does Tomo
have an amazing voice,
she is like beyond supportive
when you're singing.
Sometimes she'll
even sing back up.
Right... forgot about her...
Tomo, the air friend.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
No reason...
No reason at all.
So, both of them have
been karaoke-ing before...
Sena... Have you never
been to one?
Oh, yeah, no...
Who cares, though?!
I put the
class in classy,
so why would I do something
so unsophisticated?
Gimmie some credit. I would
never do that, like ever.
I may not have ever
been invited to go.
But I was fine because
I didn't want to.
Easy! No one
said you wanted to.
Kodaka...! Rika has
never been to karaoke...
But Rika would very
much like to go along.
Rika imagines it would
be rather difficult
to go into a place
like that all alone.
Perhaps next time
you would consider
taking Rika to
karaoke with you.
Sure...! Sounds
good to me.
Really? Thank you!
Wait...! I'm here too!
Plus, if you wanna know
the best place to go,
you should stick with me.
That's nice of
you to offer...
Thanks, Yozora.
Excuse me...
I've never been to one of
those karaoke box places either.
All of this talking about
singing has put me
in the mood to perform
"Chaos Requiem".
Well, when do
you wanna go...?
No one has anything
to do tomorrow, do they
I suppose I could make
time to go after noonish.
Rika's available
all day long.
So is Yukimura.
Tomorrow it is, then...
When and where
should we meet up?
My favorite karaoke
box is a ten-minute walk
from the Tooya
Nishi station.
Cool... Then let's meet
in front of the ticket gates
at the station?
Perfect. What time?
Wait! Hold on just a
second...! Cuz, I, um...
You um what, Meat...?
At the moment, we're
trying to make plans
to go to a karaoke
box together...
You know, that unsophisticated
disgusting place
your classy lady lumps
wouldn't be caught dead in.
Don't tell me
you've changed your mind
and want to go with us.
Look, Lumpy, unless you're
a wealth of karaoke info...
You're interrupting
a conversation
that has nothing
to do with you.
So why don't you take a
seat and shut up for once.
No, I'm not...
Uh...
The place I'm thinking of
has free play time tomorrow...
It starts at one, so why
don't we all meet up then?
Make sure you eat
lunch before you go.
Stop ignoring me!
Oh, I'm sorry...
I just assumed you
were telling the truth
when you said you
didn't want to go with us
but obviously
you were lying...
Way to put
the ass in class.
No... I wasn't lying!
Hey... We don't
care either way.
So, if you wanna go, go.
Come on.
Admit it; you want
to, don't you?
Um... Yes. I do...
I... I want to go.
I, can't hear you!
I... I want to go, too!
I'm sorry...? What was that?
I said I wanna go with
you guys to karaoke!
I see...
Well, I can certainly
understand that...
But the reality is,
I don't really want
you to go with us.
Although I suppose
I can make an exception...
All you have to do is beg.
What?? Beg??
Just say... "Please
take me with you."...
Put some heart into it.
Please. Take me with you...
Uh... I would appreciate it...
Please... Take me with you.
You know what... I
couldn't hear you like at all.
And don't forget the
most important part
is the begging part.
Oh, Yukimura...? Would you
get Rika another cup of coffee?
Louder, saggy bags!
You need to start
begging like you mean it!
Okay, fine! I'm
officially begging! .
Please let me go, too!
That wasn't
so hard, huh...?
But, still... No.
What do I have
to do you Harpy?!
I'm going whether
you like it or not! .
Plus, why would I need
your permission to go
anywhere in
the first place?!
Took you long enough
to realize that...
Gah you really are mentally
challenged, aren't you?
You're the worst!
You witch! .
I hope you die!
Now that she's gone,
you guys wanna go ahead
and decide on the real time
and place we should meet.
Are you like the devil?
It was just a joke.
I have an appointment
tomorrow at one.
So I will need to have
lunch prepared early.
Appointment...?
Would that be with
those friends of yours?
No, of course it's not.
It's with the
Neighbor's Club.
If I don't go,
they'll be lost without me.
It's tragic, really.
What is the club
planning to do?
Karaoke...
I'm going to ambush
Yozora and Kodaka
with my gorgeous,
gorgeous singing voice...
I also really want to
do a duet with Kobato! .
She's adorable!
Did you say Kodaka?
Tooya Nishi...
Please step away
from the doors.
Why are you wearing that
today-aren't you on fire?
A true heir of the
Night Tribe transcends
even the hottest of heat.
I doubt she even
knows what that means.
Look... They're all here.
Last but not least.
Are you ready?
Why are you
guys so early...?
We've still got ten
minutes before one.
I wasn't first; I got here
five minutes after Rika did.
Well, I only arrived
twenty minutes before you did
because I'm
your sidekick.
Rika managed to beat Sena
to our meeting place
by fifteen minutes.
But I was still here fifteen
minutes before Yukimura.
Why are you guys talking
like you're in the middle
of some math
word problem...
Okay... Try to figure out
who got here at what time
based upon what
they all just said.
Come on, it'll
be fun for you.
Now, we arrived at
exactly twelve fifty.
You have until we get to
the karaoke place to answer.
What?!
Um...
You forget all I need to do
is access the Akashic Records,
and solving a
problem like this one
shall be a breeze...
Watch and learn,
mere mortal...
Why do you have to use
the powers of darkness
on everything?
Ohmigah, are
we almost there?
Shut up, Meat,
and yes we are...
So, what's the name
of this place anyway?
Oh, it's "Cry
from the Abyss".
That doesn't make
Rika feel safe.
Run, Taka!
What's taking so long?
Wait for me...!
How are you so fast?
Kodaka... What the hell?
You okay?
-I'll get it this time!
-Yeah.
Go get it!
Karaoke BoxCry
From the Abyss
Good afternoon.
Wow, we're actually
at a karaoke box.
Drink bar and... Free time!
One sec... There are six
of you total, is that right?
Oh... Yeah... Six total.
Well all righty then...
The total for free time
and drinks for six people
is fifty four hundred yen.
Yes...! I've got
it big brother!
Well, free time for one
person is six fifty,
and the drink
bar is two fifty,
so that's nine per person.
That's a lot...
Just so I'm
clear on this...
We got there at
twelve fifty...
Isn't that right...?
That's what you said, isn't it?
Hey, what's wrong?
The total doesn't
make sense.
Why? What do you mean?
The price for the drink
bar is pretty much
the only thing that
does make sense...
Get this...
We're only using one room
but they wanna charge
each of us to use it.
Is that not normal?
Meat... What do you go
to a karaoke box to do?
Well um to sing
some songs, right?
Exactly!
It's still one room,
whether one person sings
thirty songs, or
six people sing five.
It's thirty songs
total regardless.
So, why do we have to
pay six times as much
for what we could get
cheaper on our own?
So basically, it's a scam.
Yeah, I think
that's their game...
You know what's
like really weird;
they never charged me twice
when I came here with Tomo.
Are you insane...?
She's not real; why would
they charge her?!
Besides that, all karaoke
boxes charge per person.
It's perfectly normal.
No way. It's
definitely a scam.
I don't want to,
but I have to agree.
My daddy said
to me once...
People who know better
should never overlook
the unnatural movement
of money so...
I know... Exactly what
we should do about this.
Hey, not bad for a
flotation device. Thanks.
You can forget what
I said about six people.
The usual...
I'm going to want free time
and drinks in my own room.
I'm acquainted
with these people,
but I'm not actually
here with them.
We just walked in
at the same time.
Okay...
One person
it is, then.
Hey. Dude... This
is my first time.
I wanna get free time and
drinks for only me, thanks.
That's weird...
What are they doing?
Rika supposes they want
us to each have
our own singing room.
Aren't they kinda
missing the point
of us coming together?
Great. Same price
for you, then...
Focus, Kodaka...
It's your turn.
We're gonna go on ahead.
So... Are you by
yourself as well?
No... Four, please.
Four people in just one
room? Are you sure?
Uhh... Yeah... Four.
Thank you so much, sir!
That's cool, right?
Yes! Let's sing a duet!
I don't care as long as
I'm in the same room
that you are.
I believe it's time
for you to finally hear
my rock star voice!
Wonderful... I need to make a
member card for you real quick.
Cool... Thanks.
everything all right?
Yeah... Everything is perfect.
Will that be
cash or credit?
Oh... Cash please.
Wow, this is so cool... Look.
Yay!
You should go
first, Kodaka! .
Rika wants to hear
what you sound like!
Me...? Gimmie
just a minute...
Come on and load the room
full of your awesome juices!
Rika, gross.
Rika's putting this large,
hard black thing right here.
Stop! Just call it a mic!
Here I go...
Go, Kodaka!
♪ How can I believe
in my reality? ♪
♪ When everything I see
is so sublime to me? ♪
♪ Is this the life you knew? ♪
♪ The one you spoke of? ♪
♪ So many questions start to
burn and turn inside my head ♪
♪ And I know it's
hard for us to speak ♪
♪ When all I've done
is neglect you. ♪
♪ But this time, I'm
gonna stay for good. ♪
♪ You and I, we're gonna
make it through... ♪
That was great!
I didn't know you had
such a wonderful voice!
It really was the most
beautiful thing...
Rika thinks
she might be wet!
This reminds me of the
time when we went running
through the moonless night
together, seven years ago.
Really? Because
I don't remember that.
It's Rika's turn!
[Music]
As we race toward the dawn
and the night starts to fade,
I'll stay with you forever,
please don't run away.
No more consequences, no
more concerns of what's fair.
Let me melt away
your problems... ?
I wonder if the girls
are singing now, too...
All alone.
Did you like my loving
up the microphone finish?
Did you feel a tingle?
Absolutely not!
Awww... Rika spent all night
working on it, though!
I'm up next.
And I'm dedicating this
song to you, Big Brother.
That's nice...
We'll, have at
it, Yukimura.
I wonder if I went in
their rooms to hear them
if they'd get
pissed off at me.
Get out! They have my
favorite song ever!
That's fantastic. ?
♪ When you feel
so alone and sad, ♪
♪ all you want... ? ♪
I hope you mortals
are ready for this! ?
♪ Rain is falling ♪
♪ and every dream of
love starts to fade ♪
♪ The memories are
all we have now. ♪
♪ We had something, ♪
♪ A friendship
that could last ♪
♪ through the
bad and good, ? ? ♪
♪ but then you walked away. ♪
♪ Promises were made, ♪
♪ but now they've all
become so broken, ♪
♪ and the bond was lost, ♪
♪ the day you turned
your back on me.? ? ♪
♪ There are no
words that I could ♪
♪ say to keep
you here with me, ♪
♪ And it hurts to know
you would ever leave; ♪
♪ All I needed was
your sympathy.? ? ♪
♪ I was living
in a fantasy, ? ? ♪
♪ But it's over now,
'cause I set you free. ? ♪
[Music]
Ugh... My throat hurts
from all the singing.
Kodaka... Hearing your voice
so low is driving
Rika wild...
It's super sadistic and
sexy all at the same time!
Rika's correct; it's
giving me chills as well.
Huh. Hey. What's
wrong with you guys?
Why don't you
ask Fog Lights?
Whatever. She so started it.
I'm guessing this had
something to do with singing?
You know how there's a
mode that scores you...?
I was using that
the whole time.
And it ranked
all of the rooms.
When I started singing,
the name "Night"
was disgustingly all
over the top rankings.
Since that
describes her soul,
I figured it was Yozora.
I was trying to fill up
all the slots with my name
until Sena the Gross
just had to show up,
unwanted, and ruin
everything as usual.
Because that's
what she does.
Seriously? You were in separate
rooms and still fighting?
So then, who ended up
with the highest rank?
Me, obviously.
What are you
talking about?
I had the top score
at ninety-nine.
Like that means
anything...
I totally dominated
ranks two through eleven
with a ninety-eight
on every one.
Who cares! First
place is first place! .
On top of winning first
I had more ninety-sevens
than you did.
Liar...! Evil must
be eating your brain
because I had like way
more ninety-sevens!
Just cause you say it
doesn't make it true.
Whatever! You wouldn't
know the truth if it hit you!
That was really
fun, wasn't it?
We should totally
do it again.
Yeah.
Thank you for coming!
I guess this is our last
club activity for the semester.
Oh yeah. I guess.
Does that mean Rika
has to wait forty days
before she can fool
around with you again?
Stop doing that, Rika!
We haven't fooled
around at all,
so quit acting like we have!
Looks like I won't get
to be your gopher
for a really
long time, then.
Jeez, what the hell are
you all freaking out about? .
The club's not gonna take
a break for the summer.
What? . We're not
taking a break...?
There a reason for that?
All of the other clubs
at school are still gonna
meet over the summer so why
would we be any different?
To start out, summer
is the normal kids'
most social time
of the entire year...
It wouldn't make sense
for us not to meet
since our goal is to make
friends with them.
We also need to keep
up with our training...
We don't want to forget
what we've already learned.
It's like the logic of
pouring boiling water
into a glass that isn't
used so it cracks, right?
Sure... Whatever you say.
Isn't that
thermal expansion?
Our next official meeting
will be on Monday...
Each of you needs to
be prepared to discuss
why you haven't been able
to make friends so far...
What is it, Twins?
The answer to your
question is you...
You're a terrible leader,
and that's why we've all failed.
You know now
that you bring it up
I have a couple
of answers myself...
First of all...
You are the most worthless
person I've ever met.
Not to mention lame
and beyond stupid.
Between your tiny brain
and your incompetence
when trying to
accomplish anything,
your existence to the club...
Technically
to the world...
is meaningless.
You are so rude!
You're right.
I said too much.
Which is funny when
you think about it,
because there aren't
enough words to describe
how much of a hazardous
waste of a person you are.
You really suck.
You're stupid;
you're annoying.
Should we leave them?
We should. Yes.
Are you sure.
Don't stop walking.
I understand, sir.
Just stop it...
Everyone's... looking....
Shut up.
No more!
Yozora, you're
such an evil...
Ugh! I hate you
and I wish you'd die!
That dumb girl is so
dramatic it's disgusting.
It's been a month
since the club started...
And none of it would have
happened without her.
Hey, Yozora?
This past month... It's
been a whole lot of fun.
Thank you.
Whatevs.
Hey Kodaka!
Wait!
What's up?
I forgot to tell
you something.
I was talking to
Daddy yesterday...
He said he had some free
time over the summer...
You can come over
and see him whenever.
I guess he's been
wanting to meet you, too.
No way, really? I'll
make sure to come by soon.
Just let me know
beforehand...
-Cool?
-Sure.
Wait. Slow your roll...
Why the hell would he
go over to your house...
And on top of that...
Why would he ever
need to meet your father?
Well, actually
it's because...
Kodaka!
I think you should
keep that a secret...
You don't want it
to cause any trouble.
Yeah, that's
a good point...
I'm sorry Sena.
She's right.
It's probably best
not to advertise
the president of the school
used his authority
to make sure
the new thug
got accepted.
So what kind of
secret is this?
The kind of secret
that has absolutely
nothing to do with you.
Whatever reason he has
to come over to my house...
And/or visit
with my father...
Well, those
are his reasons,
and he doesn't have to
explain them to anyone.
Bye, kids! I'll
see you soon, Kodaka!
Kay.
[Music]
Oh, Kodaka!
Rika is so happy
she gets to see you
over the summer break!
I'm really excited
I get to see you, too!
Don't you guys have anything
exciting planned, though?
Do you have
exciting plans?
No. Not exactly.
Rika knew it!
You know what we
should do, then...?
Pervy stuff...!
With each other.
Never fear Big Brother.
For the next forty days,
I'll be at your beck and call.
Come on!
Next! My Cell Phone
Doesn't Get Many Calls.
Hey, Where did he go?
And here we are with
no way of contacting him.