The Neighbors Club activity
report for today shows:
training camp
at the beach...
This ought to
be interesting.
Finally, I can sit down.
Me too!
I think I'll sit
here with you guys.
-Just pick one!
-Where's Rika?
Have you seen her?
Last I heard she was
looking around the train
for the Coupling section.
What the heck is that?
No! How'd I get
the Old Maid again?!
That was a prelude...
Someday soon I'll be playing
your final requiem. Be prepared.
This one!
I got the Old Maid!
That's what you get for
being a poopy vampire!
Pardon me while
I win this game.
Gimmie!
It's the stupid Old Maid!
[Music]
NO ONE SLEEPS AT CAMP
It's really
gonna take us
an hour to walk
from the station?
There's not even a bus
or a cab we can call?
That's because most normal
people just take their own car
from the train station!
Well, we're not getting
anywhere by standing here.
You coming?
Yeah, what else
are we gonna do?
Maria... , Normally in
this kind of situation,
the faculty adviser would
be the one driving us.
You know that, right?
Don't be ridiculous!
Even if I am a genius,
there's no way
I could get a
drivers license!
I couldn't reach the pedals!
Thanks for bringing it up!
You're actually
hanging in there.
I kinda thought you'd
be the first one down.
Rika had her
batteries recharged
in the Coupling section!
There was something
about the way those
strong pieces of iron
fit so tightly together.
They thrust in and
out of each other
with every movement
of the train.
It was a loud,
rough, erotic rhythm!
All that banging underneath
Rika made her feel
like getting off
and doing the nasty!
Yes! It's the Ocean!
Ocean! Ooooooocean!
We finally made it.
Wait... The beach
house is this way.
This place is amazing.
Are you sure it's okay
for us to train here?
I'm positive!
I don't want to train!
I want to swim...!
I'm gonna go
swimming, 'kay?!
Sometimes it's so obvious
what a baby you are!
We can swim
after we unpack.
Hey we're at the ocean!
We have to do that thing!
What thing?
Where we all look
out to sea,
strike a hot pose
and then we yell...
Go ocean...! Yeah!
See...? It's what we
call 'Humiliation Play.'
I don't even want to know
what that's all about
I've heard of it before!
I think one of the
characters in the video game
I was playing
was pretty into it!
Yeah I think I've
seen this too
and got really creeped out.
What does it mean,
exactly...?
Is it some ritual
for the gleeful?
Maybe that's it!
Maybe we're just not happy
enough to understand?
I don't think
that's the case,
but we should
probably practice.
That's a good idea...!
What if we come back
here with other friends
and they don't know
how to do a pose...?
We would need to know how
to show them, wouldn't we?
Is being happier really
something you can practice?
What do we do, again...?
Stare at the ocean
and yell at it...?
What would be
the point of that?
Let's give it a try.
When I give you the signal,
shout as loud as you can...
Pick any pose you
want... ready...?
I'll go first.
One... two...!
-Yay..., ocean!
-Yay, ocean!
Rika does not like
choking on salt air.
Was that supposed to
make me feel happier?
Yeah... Didn't it?
Yeah I guess so!
I think this is
the kind of thing
we should all practice
separately...
Let's put off yelling
at the ocean as a group
until we can do
it on our own... 'Kay?
How do we know if
we're good at it?
I'm being summoned
by the color blue!
Ocean waves and skies
are calling to me...!
Yay!
Kobato! Get over here
and put some sunblock on!
You know better!
Your council
makes me weary!
I must shield
my skin from sun
so that water won't hurt me.
-It's cold...! Stop...!
-You're gonna be all right.
That looks so deliciously
naughty and inappropriate!
No, it' doesn't.
You need to put
some on too.
I never carry any of
that stuff with me...
but... I think I'll be fine.
I need some...!
Cover this body in
UV barrier cream!
Uh... yeah, you look like
you'd burn pretty easily.
Brother, would you rub lotion
all over me, too please?
Of course...
You're next--right
after Maria.
I'm grateful...
and I'd like to
repay your kindness.
I can't take this!
So many naked body parts
touching each other!
It's too hot!
Even though
Yuki's nervous,
his heart beats
in anticipation!
Without even
thinking about it,
he puts his you-know-what
inside Kodoka's you-know-what .
Gently at first
and then...
It's so big...
Bigger than expected.
Excalibur!
Whatever that's
supposed to mean...
Yeah, in case
you're wondering,
I do need help putting
lotion on my back!
What...? You know there's
nothing you can do
to protect processed Meat
from going bad, don't you?
Quit treating me
like a disease!
You're so right...
I'd love to help you.
Here goes.
-Cold!
-Butch up, Prom Queen.
Your hands are like
freakishly huge;
and you can use
less lotion, you know.
It'll feel better
once you're used to it.
What...? Please...
That's what you think...
I'm used to
morons on my back.
Right. Just relax
Um... Why does it feel like
you have monkey hands?
You're imagining things.
I wish you
could feel this.
I swear I'm being
groped by a mutant.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
That's disgusting!
I wouldn't try to
get up if I were you.
Huh...? Why...? What
are you doing to me?!
I'm pressing on your
center of gravity.
No matter how hard you try,
you won't be able to move.
It's amusing, actually.
Let's discuss how
stupid it was for you
to trust me with
something like this.
I don't care! Just get
your feet off of me!
You've got the
lotion on your back.
What difference does
it make if I use my feet?
It makes a huge
difference!
No one steps on me!
I'm the one who walks
all over people!
Oh trust me.
I know that's true
and there's
nothing I enjoy more
than seeing you
get back a little of
what you've been
giving out...
Here y'go.
Does that feel better?
You're welcome.
No, that doesn't
feel better,
and it's highly
inappropriate...!
You don't get to step
on a goddess's back!
I'm the one who
does the stepping!
What's kinda weird is
I think you actually enjoy
having me on your
back like this, Meat.
Look how your
body is quivering!
Shut up, it's not true!
Stop!
I don't believe you....
You don't want me to stop...
You like feeling
helpless...
You want to be told what
to do, totally humiliated
and forced to
perform exclusively
for my entertainment.
We have words for people
like you, Boobella
-people who get pleasure
out of stuff like this... .
You're such a pervert
and now you're my slave!
I'm not a pervert.
It doesn't feel good...!
I hate this!
Oh just admit it!
You love being told what
to do, don't you,
you little bitch...?!
This is exactly
who you are!
Tell everyone
you're a pervert!
Look at you
covered in crap.
You want this.
You crave it.
Tell me! Tell me you want
to me to walk all over you!
Beg for it...! It's time
to obey your goddess,
you filthy slave!
You're crazy!
-Get off me!
-What?
Now... don't you ever say those
things about me again...!
I am not a pervert!
I'm a goddess
and a princess!
Do you understand me?!
That's hilarious...
You're funny
when you get brave.
Sena! I never knew
your ta-tas were so big!
Damn it! You are pure
evil and must be destroyed!
Well... You know where to find
me when you're ready to do it.
I hate you!
I thought for some reason
she'd be a little more
relaxed at the beach.
Got it.
Here it comes!
Catch!
Here we go.
Am I the only one who knows
how to cook around here?
Where's the yogurt?
Hey! What are you doing
out here...? You okay?
Oh... Hi, Kodaka...
So earlier today...
did you...
ya know... see... anything?
Huh...? What do you mean?
When I stood up.
Before I left.
Oh no, I was too busy putting
sunblock on Kobato
and listening
to her freak out.
Is this because of Yozora?
Is she teasing you again?
Yeah... You know
how she can be.
Forget about it...
I just made dinner for us.
Haganai
Hey! Wait up!
This feels amazing!
Let's go that way!
I'll take two
of these, please.
What are you making?
It smells kind of weird.
Paella tonight...
I bought everything on
the other side of town,
so it's much cheaper.
I'm amazed you even
know how to make that.
Yeah, it's one of Kobato's
favorite dishes so...
What about you? What kind
of things do you make...?
You took a cooking
class, didn't you?
Yeah...
but it doesn't
really matter.
All I did in that class
was stand alone
in the corner
and wait to leave.
Everyone would ignore me.
The instructor taught the
class as if I wasn't even there.
After they finished
making their meal,
they'd put a
little on my plate.
It was like they
were feeding a dog
or a homeless girl.
I'd eat it anyway
because I was hungry,
but it was humiliating.
I'd always be the first
one to finish eating
and then I would get stuck
washing everyone else's dishes.
So that's all I ever
learned in cooking class.
Wow... that's terrible.
I'm impressed,
Kodoka! This is good!
Rika thinks
it's delicious!
I must say, you've out
done yourself this time, Sir!
It was so sweet of him
to make this for us.
Shut up you
stupid vampire!
What the heck
did I do to you?!
And now back to
the weather...
Looks like tonight's the
last of our training camp.
Now that we're going home
I'm realizing we never did
any of the things you're
supposed to do on these trips.
Is there an activity
list or something?
We practiced looking at
the ocean and yelling at it.
What more do you
want from us?
And how does that
count as normal?
For what it's worth...
Rika would like to
do more before we go!
Like what?
Like... when a girl is cold
and she crawls into a
boy's sleeping bag... nude!
Quit being such
a weird pervert!
That hurt...
Then how about something
more predictable
like telling ghost stories
or playing truth or dare?
I'm surprised a science
chick would even be into games
or telling
ghost stories.
We all love stories
about the supernatural.
It's fascinating...
Rika may be a scientist,
but she's also just a
girl with a pure heart...
and a dirty mind.
Yeah, we've noticed that.
Someone did a dare in
Twinkle School today.
I kinda want to try it.
So let's start by
sharing scary stories.
Then after we're
totally freaked out,
we can go into the forest
and see who can
last the longest?
I like that idea.
I like whatever
Big Bro likes.
Nothing is more comforting
to me than the darkness...
I will be protected,
and am not frightened.
I'm not scared of ghosts
or haunted forests!
Let's do this!
Okay. We'll start with Rika
since it was her idea.
Rika feels guilty about
how high she's
gonna set this bar.
One night... there
was a big black book
with the words "Ultra-Mecha
written on the cover...
but inside the book it
said, "Ultra Magical!"
And... then what happened?
Nothing. That's the end.
Great... Who's next?
I believe I'm ready to go.
Scary Steamed Meat.
That sounds like
a funny story.
No, it's not. It's
actually very scary.
Who's next?!
I hope you're all wearing
thick underwear...
Because I'm about to drag
you into a pit of terror
you've never
even imagined.
That was an amazing build-up!
Why aren't you scared?!
Who's next?
I'll go...
I've been sitting
on this for a while,
but I think you
guys can handle it.
The name of it is...
The Miso Soup
Night of Terror.
That's the most hilarious
thing I've ever heard!
Killer miso soup!
Hahaha "Better watch out,
Mister Demon Monster!
I've got some soup and
I know how to use it!"
I don't get why
it's so funny.
It's not...
That's the story you
keep in your back pocket?
Do you not know
what scary is?
That's weird. I could ask
you guys the same thing.
Since you all suck
at making things up,
I'll tell a true story
then we can move on.
A friend of mine told me
about this in confidence
a long time ago.
You don't' have any
friends. This is fake.
Just shut your face!
To protect her privacy,
I'm going to call her Eiko...
This is something that's
been haunting me for years.
When Eiko was
in middle school,
she only had one
really close friend...
They were inseparable and
did everything together...
We'll call that friend
"Waiko for now...
in their hearts
they were sisters,
and only had each other.
Their school was known all
over town for being haunted.
Everyone who went
there had a story
about a ghost called Yamiko--
a past student who
died on campus.
However they say
she only haunts those
who have betrayed
their close friends.
Students who are loyal
have never seen her...
Anyone who ever
does though, dies.
Both girls liked
the same guy.
To protect their friendship,
they promised each other
they would not pursue him.
One day, Eiko
broke her promise
which drove Waiko
to commit suicide.
After that incident,
Eiko started noticing
all kinds of strange things
happening around her...
it got worse and worse...
until one day...
After that night
Eiko just disappeared
and was never
heard from again.
Okay. Is everyone ready to
go out into the forest?
We're all really tired.
I think we should
call it a night....
Plus, it's dark outside.
We might trip
or something.
Yeah, if something
happened... we'd be lost...
no one would ever find us.
It's okay guys.
We don't have to do
the bravery test.
Yozora's story really
freaked me out...
but I started to realize,
it wasn't the part about
the ghosts that kept me up.
Honestly...
It was the whole
'broken promises
leading to
suicide' thing...
I thought about my
best friend from
when I was a kid
and what he did...
It made me wonder
if he thinks
I'm the one who hurt him.
You gotta be kidding?!
Hi, Kodaka... you awake?
Sena? What are you
doing in here?
Will you come with
me...? I need a favor.
Ok, where are we going?
I... have to go to the bathroom
and the halls are dark.
What on earth?
And it's not because
I'm scared, okay!
I'm totally fine...! I
just need someone there in case,
you know, in case
I need someone there.
Why didn't you ask
Yozora to help you?
You guys are
sharing a room.
Are you crazy?!
She'd just make fun
if I asked her to
help me with this...!
So... Can we please hurry?
I'm seriously about
to pee on the floor.
Okay fine.
You're still out there,
aren't you, Kodaka?
Yeah. I'm still here.
Hey, are you
still out there...?
Kodaka are you there?
I said I was!
Well, I didn't hear
you! Stop yelling!
Are you still there?
I haven't moved.
If you tell Yozora
this ever happened,
I'll completely deny it...
And I swear, I'll
never forgive you!
'Kay. Let's go.
-You awake?
-What's the matter?
Will you please...
take me to the bathroom?
Hello? Are you
still out there?
Yep, I'm right here.
Bathroom, right?
Whoa...! That was
an amazing trick!
You must be a
psychic or something!
Big Bro! Are you
still out there?
Help! Help! Kodaka!
Yeah! Just hurry up...!
I gotta sleep
at some point.
I'm almost done!
Yes, I'll take you
to the bathroom.
Hold on.
Bathroom...? Rika
was fine with the bed,
but that sounds
much more exciting!
Go to sleep!
I should've gone while I
was up the first three times.
Whats the matter?
Are you ok?
Why are you up?
Because I have to pee.
Hey that's
funny, so do I...
And since we're both up,
why don't we go
down there together?
Don't tell me
you're scared...
You're the one who
was telling the story
why are you
so freaked out?
No I'm not!
Why would you say
something that ridiculous?!
There's nothing
to be ashamed of.
I just want to know
how you scared yourself.
Because the goal
was to scare people.
If I wasn't
affected by it,
I couldn't
guarantee they'd be.
So um...
I have a question...
You can go in
first; it's cool.
Thanks
Hey, Kodaka, are
you still out there?
I sure am.
Still there?
Yup...! Don't forget
I still have to go,
so it would be really
stupid of me to leave.
Right... That makes sense.
Sorry about that.
All good.
You don't have to ask.
I'll stay here and
wait for you to finish.
So, seriously?
You weren't affected
by my story at all?
Nope. Not even a little bit.
I'm impressed...
You're a lot braver
than I thought.
Look at that...! Wow...
But I really
did like the moral
about not betraying
your friends.
Yeah.
So did I.
[Music]
When we were
telling ghost stories,
I intentionally made my story
a little lamer than yours.
What are you
talking about?
Everyone knows I'm better
at the funny stories
so I stepped back and let
you have your moment.
Goodnight.
What's with the cut off?! Fine,
I won't tell a story then.
How about a
stand-up routine?
I'll make you laugh
till your sides hurt!
No thank you!
At least hear
the subjects!
-No.
-Oh don't be a pooper!
Next: Episode Eleven.
Girls Are Super
Cute in Yukatas!
Okay so a chicken
walks into a bar and...
Where'd you go?!