Oh, look. It's about
freakin' time.
Oh, hey.
What's up, Kashiwazaki?
Call me Sena.
Gah.
Uh. You call harpy face by
her first name, don't you?
But for whatever reason
you feel the need to
squeeze out five syllables
when you want to talk to me.
Okay, fine.
Hey. Sena.
Can we just get this
show on the road already.
-Right. Mikazu...
-It's Yozora!
Kay.
Yozora.
So. How does this
club even work?
We're just supposed
to make friends
even though none
of us know how?
Oh, I know one way
of making friends.
Video games.
[Music]
So you want us to make
friends with gamers, now?
-Because, why?
-Don't be so judgmental.
Gaming has gone way
beyond mainstream.
Check it out.
I've got a PSP
plan of attack!
Are you serious?
My little sister has that.
Last night when I went
out to dinner by myself.
You went out to eat alone?
Shut up!
Anyway, four
guys from school
were sitting at
the table behind me.
And they were all playing
this game together.
Nice! Monster Hunting!
Have you played it?
No, but it's your
basic fantasy RPG.
You get to hunt monsters.
But the cool thing is
you have the ability
to play with other
people at the same time.
If you're good at it
other players will
want to play with you,
which you can use as a
way to make new friends.
They let you
exchange items too,
so that's an easy way
to start up conversations
with people you don't know.
I get it. If we play
this game with each other.
We'll have the opportunity
to practice our friendship
making skills!
I'm not gonna make it
any dirtier than you are!
Um. Are you listening to me?
Now, bring your own
PSP in by next Monday.
Then we can all go Monster
Hunting together, you got it?
Sure, why not.
And so, the
following Monday.
You guys have both practiced
using this thing, right?
-Yeah.
-Yep.
I was busy this weekend.
But I found some time
to mess around with it.
Not for very long,
but you know how it is.
-Such is the life of me.
-Milk Cow.
Kodoka What level
are you ranked?
I'm at level, one.
I can't seem to kill
any of the bad guys.
I'm a level three.
Three? Already!
I'm six. Is that good?
-Six?
Yeah, that's good.
It's the highest level.
Seriously, how perfect
can one girl get?
I'm even a prodigy
at video games.
I thought you said you didn't
spend that much time on it.
How much "messing
with it" did you do?
Not that much.
I was barely on it at all.
Let me see for
myself, Meat Sacks.
Hey, give that back!
I didn't say you
could look at it!
Are you kidding me?
You were on it for
fifty-three hours?
I have to admit it your
outfit's pretty cute.
Too cute for a lying
show off like you.
What the hell
are you doing?
Look at that.
You've got nasty
bags under your eyes.
I do not!
I don't get bags.
I know exactly what
you're up to Meat.
You played the game the
entire weekend didn't you?
A Tigress devotes herself
to anything she does,
even stupid games.
-Tigress?
-Tigress!
Okay.
That's right.
Now. Let's play
the damn thing.
I don't mind hosting.
I'll even help
you two out
by taking us on an easy
quest, so you're welcome.
She may be another
completely crazy chick,
but at least she's
serious about the club.
Are you guys ready?
Cause I'm ready.
Sorry that took so long!
What the hell
are you wearing?
Leave me alone;
I'm just a beginner.
I can't help it, okay!
That's no excuse for
your entire character.
It's pathetic he doesn't
even look like you.
Don't take it personal,
but everything we're
looking at is a disaster.
Even your name is cheesy.
When is "Hawk"
ever a good idea?
You guys, shut up!
This is just a game,
so it can be a little bit
different from reality.
A little?
Come on.
Let's go a-hunting!
Looks like we'll get
through this level quickly.
I wonder what I
should kill this time?
What the hell was that?
Oh, silly me.
I guess I just mixed up
all of those buttons.
Oh well. Now get it together
so we can go a-hunting.
Something tells me a
player with her rank
doesn't get the
"buttons mixed up".
She probably spent
all those hours
playing for that one moment.
It was a stupid mistake
I'm not surprised.
Shall we go?
Yay!
What the hell
was that about?
Oopsie. Got my
buttons mixed up.
Whatever? You so
did that on purpose!
I so did not.
You need to relax, Meat.
Paranoia does not
look good on you.
That's it!
Look out! Here it comes!
Oh! Don't worry;
I'll take care of this guy.
Ha. I'm not about to let some
dumb lizard take me down.
Get ready,
because I, oh...
Hey! That was a
sleeping potion!
Uh. What are you doing?
Guess.
Awesome! Totally killed it!
-And hit me!
-Yeah.
I was trying to give
you a little back up.
I guess I just don't
know my own strength.
Lie! You were trying
to hit me on purpose!
Hey! We're supposed to
cooperate on this game,
so maybe we should try that!
Yeah, Hooters.
But I'll make sure to
cooperate even more next time.
Well, in that case,
brace yourself.
I'm gonna cooperate
the hell out of this.
After that.
The real hunting began.
Those meat flaps of yours
are grossing me out.
I better turn 'em
into ground beef.
Shriek away little Harpy.
Shriek.
You won't be saying
much when I kill you.
-Silence, Meat.
-No.
Because I do what I want!
Cool! I found dogrite!
I rock!
Since you're
nothing but trash,
you won't mind
licking my boots!
That doesn't even
make sense, Meat!
Someone help me!
Sorry, guys.
I just died.
Uh.
It's like I only
really feel alive
when I'm really
killing something!
I'm gonna rip
out your guts
and shove 'em right
down your throat, Harpy!
How do you like that?
In your face!
Try this on for size!!
Maybe video games
aren't right for us.
Yeah, seems like a
waste of time, right?
For real.
And since when did
PSPs become like
all about the multiplayer
games anyway?
Why should I have
to play with people
who are just
gonna die on me?
I thought playing with
people was the whole point!
I completely agree.
I don't have
a lot of time.
Why should I
have to share it?
Ugh. And with a stranger.
Yeah. Totally.
Yeah, why would you think
of anyone else besides you?
Nothing; never mind.
What do you wanna do today?
Same thing we
do every day.
Try and take
over the world.
How far'd you get
in Monster Hunting?
I didn't bring forth
imperial wrath,
but I did kill Jinrou.
I also got a ton of tail.
Here goes!
Do you have anything extra
you can share with me?
Prob'ly.
Hey, uh, guys.
So I've been playing that
Monster Hunting game, too!
Do you by chance have
the Scarf of Dos- jagira.
And would you be
willing to trade for it?
Sure; whatever you want!
Yeah. Anything else
you need say the word.
It's yours it's no
big deal at all.
Thanks guys.
That's cool.
By the following day,
the rumor had spread
through the whole school.
I had pulled a shakedown in
homeroom in broad daylight.
Okay. What's that?
Your blonde is
showing again!
They're two modern
conveniences
known as a television
and a gaming console.
They use electricity.
Yeah, that's not
what I meant.
Why did you
bring them here;
What are they doing
in the clubroom?
Um. To play a game with?
How'd you even get
the TV in here?
Anyway.
Why would you want to
bring them to school to play
in the first place?
I found a game that's one:
not a piece of crap
like Monster Hunter,
and two: looked useful to us.
So, I figured
I'd bring it in.
Be grateful, you ingrates.
Shut up, Coconuts you're
ruining my coffee.
Hey! That's not coffee;
it's tea.
And it's also not yours!
Sparkling School Life.
Seven?
Sounds like one of
those chick games to me.
It's a game about making
new friends, stupid.
So it is.
This could be good for us to
practice casual conversations.
Yeah, it's for guys
to meet girls, though.
Didn't they have one
for you all to practice
meeting hot dudes
to be friends with?
Why?
What would be the point
of being friends with guys?
Right. Thank you.
Sparkling School
Life Seven!
All right. S-E-N-A.
Excuse me?
Why the crap do we have
to use your nasty name?
I mean, I'm the public
face of this club.
We should be
using my name.
You're the club's
public face?
Well that explains
why no one's joining.
Uh. The main
character is a guy,
so maybe we should
use my name?
Hell no.
Well, at least they're
agreeing on something.
Fine. Sena is the one who
brought the game here for us.
I think we should
just go ahead
and use her name this time.
Gah, whatever.
Way to use your
head, Kodaka.
Okay. Kashiwazaki.
Sena.
Sorry; changed my mind.
There.
Ugh. You're such a jerk ass.
Hi! I'm Semoponume Kashiwazaki.
What the hell
is Semoponume?
Come on, I think it's
a lovely random name.
You should change
your real name to that.
Seriously Sena
makes me want to puke
like every time I say it.
Dude! Semoponume!
This guy's name
is Masaru Suzuki.
We've been best friends
since middle school.
What? You're kidding me?
This douche already
has a best friend?
And that selfish son
of a bitch has the balls
to say he wants even more?
Stop making
that creepy face.
And move outta the way.
The best way to have the
best time in high school
is to cozy up next
to a pretty girl!
Go get one!
That guy's a player,
but he is so right.
I'd love to have a pretty
friend to cozy up to!
Hello. Nice to meet you.
My name is Akari
Fujibayashi.
I was nervous about
starting this new school,
but I am now happy
that I am sitting next to
such a nice looking guy.
Would you like to be my friend
at this time, Semo-ponume?
Oh. So you get to choose
how the guy answers.
Number three.
How come three?
Doesn't that seem rude?
No, not when some
hussy you don't know
tries to get all
up on your stuff
on the first day of school.
You can't trust
girls like that.
True.
I bet she probably says
the exact same thing
to every single guy
in the classroom.
Aw, come on. She doesn't
look that bad to me.
Of course she doesn't.
Bitches never look
like bitches at first.
But there's one of
her in every class.
She looks so innocent,
but all she's really doing
is playing every guy in school.
Is there one her
of in our class?
Totally.
Online it says practically
every high school girl
is a big bitch these days.
Surely she realizes she
qualifies as a high school girl.
Okay, number three it is.
What a pushy broad!
Get lost!
Oh my. I am so sorry.
As it is our
first time meeting,
I may have been too forward.
I will be more
careful from now on,
so I hope that you
are not mad at me.
Akari. I'm so sorry.
Hey ho, let's go!
So basically, you get to
decide what you wanna do,
and if you make
the right choice,
you get to talk to girls.
This game is a rough
place for a guy
who can't gain
enough merit points
to get a girl to
go out with him.
It's just like reality.
He needs to
get good grades
so no one thinks he's stupid.
Let's start with
making him study.
Good idea.
I hate boys who are
cerebrally-challenged.
The more he studies
the smarter he gets.
Wow. How big of an idiot was
this dude to start out with?
Give the poor guy a break;
it's just a game.
Look! Someone's here!
Oh. I am sorry.
Another choice?
I bet they go with two.
So, which one is it?
Number one.
Seriously?
Instead of wasting time
reading random books
he needs to be
focused on studying.
I'm aiming for two
hundred academic points
by the next test.
So no screwing
around, loser.
Naturally.
No, I'm sorry.
You are kind.
Thank you.
May I have your name if
you don't mind too much?
Sure. I'm Semoponume Kashiwazaki
from Class D.
Semoponume Kashiwazaki.
That is a very nice name.
Jeez, talk about
having terrible taste.
It's scary.
For now, I'm thinking we oughta
be friends with this girl.
Are you okay with that?
Yeah. She's way better than
that Fujibayashi bitch.
Go ahead.
Yukiko.
Yes?
She's so cute;
I can't stand it!
And she likes me?
Is there anything
better in the world
than having a girl like you?
Yeah. Plus she looks like
she's like a good person.
Yukiko. Let's walk
home together.
I. No.
I am sorry!
I don't understand.
What's wrong Yukikio?
I guess this
was the reason
Yukiko Nagata suddenly
became so cold.
What? Tell me!
You know how every time
you saw that Akari girl
you were really
mean to her?
Apparently that caused a
nasty rumor go through school.
A rumor saying that
you're mean to girls
and therefore not
to be trusted.
So basically, the reason
Yukiko doesn't like me
is because that
stupid bitch Akari
has been bad mouthing me all
over the whole damn school!
I hate her so
freaking much!
I think you might
be exaggerating.
It says here if
you get a bad rep,
you need to find out who
doesn't like you and apologize.
What?
Why the hell would
I ever apologize
to such an awful person?
This is ridiculous;
I don't even
want to be friends
with that disgusting
cow in the first place.
Totally agree.
How is this our fault that
we need to say we're sorry?
By no means am I about to
bow down to some idiotic female
who's just talking trash
because she got shot
down for acting slutty.
Yeah, like for
real, right?
I refuse to
give in on this.
And I have total faith that
Yukiko will understand anyway.
Yukiko. Please, I...
I am sorry.
Goodbye forever!
Wait, no!
I had faith in her.
But... But she
still let me down.
She's really crying.
Why do I only
get the crazies?
Hey. Where are you
off to, Yozora?
To find Akari Fujibayashi.
And kill her.
Are you okay?
Yukiko? Why?
Good morning!
-Hey, Kodaka!
-Hmm?
Over here!
Here!
I'm letting
you borrow that,
so be sure and play it
as soon as you get home.
And definitely watch out
for the third year event
with Akari Fujibiyashi;
it's particularly moving.
Akari?
But isn't she
the poor girl
you kept calling a
stupid bitch yesterday?
Do not talk like
that about her!
I'm sorry?
Listen.
She's been through.
Well, a lot since her
parents were killed.
That girl's the
strongest girl I know.
She won't let
anything get her down.
The only thing in her
heart is a ball of love.
Is that so?
Oh! You have to make
sure you capture Yukiko!
Actually Miho, Natsumi,
Mizuki and Karen.
They're all amazing girls.
Okay. So after going
home yesterday,
you conquered all of them?
Obviously.
Be sure you pay close attention
to how they all end, too.
You got that?
Sure. I'll give it a whirl
if I'm in the mood to play it.
No way.
You will play it whether
you're in the mood or not.
You have to.
It's an experience everyone
should be a part of.
It's not just a game,
it's a work of art!
Don't you understand?
It's life held
in your hand.
Oh no! I'm gonna be late!
And you better play it!
Oh crap!
Neighbors Club Record.
Sena became friends with
seven different girls.
All of whom are
two dimensional.
[Music]
Hey, boob face.
About those chick games.
Did you know people
who play them in the middle of
the night get brainwashed?
What? They do?
Yep. Their brainwaves end up
getting controlled by the game,
and they lose their
normal sense of judgment,
which means they never
make any friends.
That is not true!
On top of that, their hair
turns a gross blond color
and the fat on their chest
expands turning them into cows.
Is that for real?
Of course not.
You're stupid.
Says the idiot.
Next: There Are no Flags
at the Swimming Pool.
Why pool?