Yo.
What's up?
[YUKIMURA]
Good afternoon, Big Brother.
[KODAKA] Yukimura, what are you
doing in that butler get-up?
It's part of the training
that's listed in
"Becoming a Real Man"
Volume Two.
Though my skills have not quite
matured, I am devoted, Sir.
Look, this has nothing
to do with maturity.
You're a girl.
You can't do this.
My body's simply a home
for my heart, sir.
A true man can
transcend biology.
Don't let anyone
tell you differently.
Science determined
that you're female,
but the truth of your
soul knows who you are.
If in your heart you
long to be the man you admire,
don't let that dream go!
Thank you.
I'm going to make you
proud of me.
I'll never give up.
You're my inspiration.
I hope to be a man,
just like you, someday.
[KODAKA]
Okay.
I can appreciate
your dedication,
but the clothes
don't make sense.
What's with the butler thing?
[YOZORA] A butler represents
the most capable man.
Capable of what?
Who cares?
It's fine.
Girls in butler costumes are
totes adorable and you know it.
Especially pretty girls.
It's actually become kind of
a popular trend lately.
Like Black Butler.
Everyone loves that so you're
instantly cool if you dress
like those characters--even
the girls.
Or like that Chicken Butler
and Mayonnaise show!
All girls want
to be Kokonoe Mebaru!
[SENA] I love how even though
she tries to act all sophist,
she can't hide
how awkward she is.
And if she's pissed,
everyone knows about it!
[RIKA]
Everything she does is so sexy!
The way she manages to get
covered in mayonnaise every
five seconds and has to change
her shirt makes me think
'Oh you want it bad,' ya know?
And Rika knows she
would say 'yes' to that!
[SENA]
I wish I was as cute as Mebaru!
[RIKA]
I mean, is there anyone hotter?
So yeah, that was a good
call you made, Yozora!
Yukimura in a butler suit
is going to do wonders
for her social life.
Great.
Guess I screwed that up, too.
I'm sorry, that all
went over my head,
but I'm pleased to wear
the clothes I was given.
I only hope they allow me
to serve you as best as I can.
Right on.
Well, you have my support.
[KODAKA]
What are you doin?
Looks like one of those
"Boys Love" games.
Yes, it is.
Rika thought she'd try
to sort through some of
her game backlog while she can.
[KODAKA]
Are they all dude on dude games?
[RIKA]
No, not all.
There are some RPGs, some
shooters, and some otomege, too!
Wait, what was that last one?
Otomege?
What's that?
Where the main character
is a girl and she tries to
date as many boys as she can.
No!
It's-- it's that game.
The Semoponume crap from before!
That looks familiar.
Is it a spinoff of
Sparkling School or something?
Well, color Rika impressed!
This is the otomege version
of Sparkling School Life,
where the main character's
and target characters' genders
are flipped.
Kind of the Girl Version.
They call it
"Girl School" for short.
Ah.
There are all kinds of
crazy games in this world,
aren't there?
Why does Rika get the feeling
you're not interested?
Oh, because I'm not.
You said it's related
to that crap game,
and I'm sure
it's just as trashy.
[SENA]
That's it.
We're in a fight!
Look, I've never played Girl
School, but neither have you and
you're practically peeing
all over Sparkling School's
little sister!
Which means you may as well
be peeing all over
my little sister.
That's fine.
I hope you're happy
having peed all over Kobato.
Except Kobato's not your sister.
Not the point.
I don't think it's right for you
to decide you don't like it
when you haven't played it yet.
So, you're on their side?
Fine.
I'll decide I hate it after I've
played it--and I will hate it.
But then you'll have
to accept that it sucks.
[VIDEO GAME]
Sparkling School Life.
Girls Version.
Four.
[SENA] Why are you
skipping the opening?
That's one of the best parts!
[YOZORA]
'Cause it's lame.
What?
I have to pick a name?
Just use your real name.
That's what everyone else does.
Makes it more real.
But the main character's
some tramp who's trying to get
with a bunch of guys.
Why would I want to be that?
It'd be way better to play
with Meat's name.
Oh ha ha, you're so funny!
It's fun to play the wild girl.
But you can also be the nice one
and limit yourself to one guy.
It would be fun to see one
of them take your V-card!
Well, that doesn't seem
that bad, I guess.
[SENA]
Your name is Yohechiborake!
Weirdest name in the world for
the weirdest girl in the world!
[KODAKA] She must still
be bitter about the whole
"Semoponume" thing.
[SENA]
I'm so freaking brilliant!
[RIKA]
It's not that funny.
What?
Why are you sabotaging Rika's
efforts to spread the gospel
of Girl School?
All you're doing is turning
others away from our tribe.
Oh.
I just thought
it was a funny name.
[RIKA]
Why would you do that?
Because-- I, uh.
Look, I said I was sorry.
Rika's not asking you
to apologize.
She just wants to know why
you would do something
wicked like that.
She's asking you nicely.
[KODAKA]
Girls are scary.
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
My name is Yozora Mikazuki.
Starting today,
I'm a high school freshman
here at Sparkling Academy!
Ah!
The spring breeze feels so nice!
Um.
Spring breeze?
[IN-GAME YOZORA] Even though
I'm just an average every day
student, nothing would make
me happier than having
an exciting school life!
My breasts are heaving with
hope as I make my way through
the gates laden
with cherry blossoms.
Did you just say your breasts
are heaving with hope?
A, that was cheesy;
B, you don't have breasts!
That wasn't very
"Spring Breezy" of you.
I'll kill you.
Calm down.
Heckling is part of gaming.
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Ouch!
[IN-GAME BOY]
I'm sorry.
I was daydreaming.
Here, can you stand?
Well that was nice.
Who is this boy?
Ouji Shinomori.
He's a star freshman
just like your character.
He's the heir to the
Shinomori Conglomerate,
which means every girl in
school wants to be with him.
[OUJI SHINOMORI]
Nice to meet you.
I'm hoping this year will
be great for both of us.
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
That boy was really cool.
If I already met someone
like him on my first day,
then the rest of the year
is looking sweet as roses!
What a sweet, rosy red year
you have ahead of you!
Okay, I'm gonna let you pick.
Which name do you like
better--Rosy or Spring Breeze?
I am not using my name on the
flowerbed for brains idiot.
How do I switch it
back to the other one?
Whoa!
It's just a game!
The dialogue is the same
no matter who's playing!
[IN-GAME GIRL]
Oh hey!
So like, how do you
know Shinomori?
[YOZORA] Who the hell
is this random hag?
[KODAKA] Yoko sits next
to the player in class.
Refer to her with questions
about other students.
Um.
I think I'll refer to her
with my fist instead.
She's a bit of an A-hole.
[KODAKA]
She was being nice!
Yeah, way too soon!
You don't get to walk up
to a random stranger
and act like you're besties.
That is a cocky, punk-ass move.
She's just like Akari!
What's your deal?
Akari's like,
the sweetest girl in the world!
[YOKO]
I like you, Yozora.
Let's be friends, okay?
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Sure!
It's nice to meet you!
She is so fake.
She's so gonna
stab me in the back.
I just know it.
Low scores in all
areas except sleeping?
Loser.
Guess I'll build up
her grades first.
That's better.
Almost done.
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Hm.
This question's a hard one.
Oh shut up.
You're never gonna make it
anywhere if you can't get
through level one
freshman homework.
Man, I hate this game.
It's not challenging.
[IN-GAME BOY 2] You look
like you're having trouble.
Want me to explain that to you?
Hot boy with glasses!
Win!
Is that the Girl School
version of Yukiko?
That dude kind of sucks.
His name is Touma Suzutsuki.
He has the highest GPA
in the class.
Oh, well, that's cool.
He can help you
with homework, right?
Great.
[TOUMA SUZUTSUKI] So I think
it's great that you study in the
library in your free time, and I
can't stop thinking about you.
Wha-- What does that mean?
He may look like a smart guy,
but he's actually
just a huge perv!
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Get out of the way!
I'm busy!
[TOUMA SUZUTSUKI]
I admire you for wanting
to solve such a difficult
problem on your own.
However, there's nothing
wrong with asking for help
once in awhile.
The greatest minds do it.
Please don't hesitate to call
if you change your mind.
Does anybody else
find him annoying?
Guess I'm gonna have
to find somewhere else
to study besides the library.
Ugh!
Yes!
Now that's more like me!
Yeah, but it's a dating game and
you killed your social skills.
Rika finds it painful
to watch someone fail
so miserably this way.
She wants to cry.
Even in games
she's a tragic mess.
Really?
You punks must have a death wish
if you're coming after me when
I have a strength level
of three hundred and eighty!
Take this!
What the crap?
Come on!
Why isn't the
attack button working?
I think you're confused as to
what kind of game this is.
[IN-GAME BOY 3]
Ugh.
I'm gonna be honest.
Guys like you seriously
make me wanna puke.
[DELINQUENT 1]
Bastard!
[DELINQUENT 2]
Get him!
[IN-GAME BOY 3]
You're Yozora Mikazuki, right?
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
How do you know my name?
[IN-GAME BOY 3]
You are famous, you know.
The name's Eiji Nagatani.
This ain't the place
for elite types like you
to be wandering around.
You should go home.
[YOZORA]
Maybe I should ask him out!
[RIKA]
You should!
But does that mean
this type of guy is your type?
Of course not!
I'm just trying to make
this game more interesting
since you're forcing me to play.
So shut up.
Guys like that creep me out
with their messy hair,
crazy eyes, and boring voices.
They're also extremely rude.
[GIRLS snapping]
Oh shut up and sit down!
[EIJI NAGATANI]
Huh?
You mean next Sunday?
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Right.
Let's meet-- Um,
how about the batting cages?
[EIJI NAGATANI]
Sure.
That's fine, I guess.
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Okay, it's a date.
[EIJI NAGATANI]
Wow, you're pretty good.
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Anyone can do this much!
[EIJI NAGATANI] You did your
hair different today, huh?
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Hm?
Did you say something?
[EIJI NAGATANI]
Huh?
It was nothing.
Wow.
He's actually pretty
observant for a commoner.
I'm impressed.
Maybe Kodaka would benefit
from taking some
lessons from that guy.
Lessons in what?
Noticing girls' hairstyles!
When they take the time
to do something different
with their hair,
you should mention it,
and follow that
with a compliment!
I do that anyway.
Ask Yozora.
When you cut your hair,
I said it looked nice, right?
I don't remember!
Why would you
bring that up now?
So you complimented
Yozora's hair.
Rika gets it.
[KODAKA]
And while we're on the subject,
I noticed you've been changing
yours around a lot lately.
You noticed this whole time
and never said anything?
You never once reacted so
Rika was afraid that she was
as memorable as
a rock on the roadside!
She has lost many nights
of sleep and suffers
massive depression
because you're stupid!
I'm sorry, chill out!
It's just-- there's never
a time I'm not watching you.
Commenting would get old.
[KODAKA] I can't let you
out of my sight
or you'll blow something up.
It's way too late to win Rika
over with that line of crap!
Maybe if you'd worked on
your status this whole time.
[KODAKA]
Status of what?
What do you mean?
I mean if you'd spent a
little more time building
your affection points with Rika,
you'd be going at it with her
right now in a loud, passionate
cacophony of pleasure.
As it is, your points are very
low and she cannot credit you
for this mild excuse
for a compliment.
If you bring those points up,
you'll get yourself up!
But why should I have to win
affection points from you?
We're friends, aren't we?
'Cause I said so!
Wait, let's talk about this!
Rika is hurt and
needs to be alone
to practice some self-love.
'Kay thanks, bye.
Uh, what does
she mean by 'self love?'
Exactly what you think.
Rika's a pervert.
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
Another fun day, huh?
[EIJI NAGATANI]
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Uh, what is happening here?
I don't wanna be presumptuous,
but he seems nervous,
like he might like me?
Well, there are definitely
feelings going on over there.
So then, yes, he does like me?
[EIJI NAGATANI]
Listen, Yozora.
I think we should
stop seein' each other.
Wha--?
[EIJI NAGATANI] I mean, you're
like the school super-star.
Shoot, they even made you
student body president.
You keep hangin' out
with a punk like me,
it'll destroy your reputation.
[IN-GAME YOZORA]
You are such a wuss!
Who cares what other people
decide to think of me?
I'll decide who I want to
be with, do you understand?
So you have to stay with me!
I never saw it coming, but I
actually feel sorry for Yozora.
Me too.
[KODAKA] If she keeps playing,
maybe-- Maybe they'll make up?
[IN-GAME YOZORA] I got into
a first-rate university,
but I didn't manage
to get close to anyone.
It was a lonely three years.
It was my own fault.
I should've tried
harder to make friends.
That was the worst ending ever!
What's going to
happen to Eiji now?
[RIKA]
Rika is afraid at some point
you must have failed
to clear a key checkpoint.
You were never seen interacting
with any of the other boys,
or even Yoko for that matter.
[YOZORA]
Oh yeah.
Don't get too down
on yourself about it.
That's what's
great about gaming.
You can learn from
your mistakes and try again!
Next time you can
come on to them hardcore
and play the vixen!
[YOZORA]
Yeah.
No thanks.
I'm over it.
If this is what happens
when I get to choose how
I live my life, that's fine.
But I am sorry that
I called it a crappy game.
Girl School was actually fun.
I didn't expect that.
Oh, and P.S?
I can barely stand the
pansy-core guys in my real life.
I don't need to
create more in a game.
Hey guys, what's up?
Good morning, Kodaka.
How are you doing today?
I'm good.
You changed your
hairstyle, didn't you?
That's all you've got?
What do you want from me?
I noticed you changed
your hair, didn't I?
You did.
But what did Rika
change about it?
Was it the way she's
wearing it or the color
or did she cut some inches off?
Or maybe it's all three?
Did you trim it a bit?
This is more than a trim!
I know, gosh.
I was just kidding.
Give me a second.
Oh!
You're a tricky one!
You had Rika going!
You bought some new hair ties.
It's more than that. Jerk!
Okay, spill it.
What's with the bimbo look?
You over being smart?
Absolutely not.
Rika just wanted
to experiment with color.
[KODAKA] That's bad for
your hair, you know.
Not to worry!
Rika used a hair dye formula
she created all by herself!
[KODAKA]
You made it?
[RIKA] Rika is quite
proud of this one!
There is almost zero fading or
risk of damage in this formula!
And the most amazing feature
is you can switch back
to your natural color
anytime you decide to.
Isn't that awesome?
[KODAKA] Yeah, I guess
it's kinda awesome,
but if I'm being totally honest,
your inventions lately,
they're not blowing me away.
Like which ones?
Well, computer software,
long-lasting light bulbs,
electric pots that boil water
without a heat source,
automatic beetle-raising tanks,
ice cream without calories,
and now reversible hair dye.
I mean don't get me wrong,
they're all very
useful products.
But where's the sparkle?
Where's the romance?
Fine.
What kind of invention
do you want from Rika?
Well, I never thought about it.
Oh!
I know.
How about one of those
giant robots you like?
That's a national-government
level project!
It'd take Rika years
to get that approved!
Oh.
Then how about a
fifth-dimensional pocket?
The difficulty level on that one
far exceeds your robot idea.
All right then.
Maybe a flashlight that can
make things bigger or smaller?
Or maybe like a cloth,
and you can wrap it around
broken items to fix them?
Or a jelly you can
eat and understand
any language you want.
Do they make those yet?
No, scratch that!
How do you feel
about time machines?
Wha--?
[RIKA] Ladies and gentleman,
Rika gives you: Time Machine!
Huh?
That's a time machine?
Can you go to both the past
and the future with it?
Unfortunately
there's no future mode.
Travelers may
only visit their past.
[KODAKA]
You're kidding, right?
If you don't believe Rika,
put it on and try it yourself!
Now don't freak out in there.
Rika will bring you
back after five minutes.
Um.
Okay.
Be careful.
Have you ever tested that
thing to make sure it's safe?
Rika is a mad scientist.
You have nothing
to worry about--gah!
Yeah, the word 'mad'
isn't very reassuring.
Don't sweat the
small stuff, Kodaka.
Now, Rika needs you to
concentrate and think of
what part of your past
you want to revisit.
[KODAKA] I know exactly
where I want to go.
[KODAKA]
No way.
That's amazing.
[YOUNG YOZORA] What are you
mumbling about over there?
Wow.
It's really her.
What's going on Taka?
Huh?
But-- I.
Uh.
Wha--?
Are you having a seizure?
No, I'm fine.
It was just some gas.
You're so weird.
All right, well.
Don't forget tomorrow.
I gotta go home now.
[KODAKA]
I can't believe it worked.
I'm in that exact day.
Have a good night, Taka.
[YOUNG KODAKA]
Yozora, wait!
How do you know
what my real name is?
Listen.
My family and I are
moving day after tomorrow.
I won't be back
for around ten years.
So that means tomorrow will
be my last chance to see you!
Really?
I'm sorry!
[KODAKA]
For leaving you alone.
But we'll stay friends!
Even if we don't
see each other anymore.
[KODAKA] Except you forgot
about her until you came back.
No matter what, I promise
I'll never forget you!
[KODAKA] And then you
couldn't even place her face
once you did.
I'm sorry!
I really am.
[KODAKA]
And I always will be very sorry.
[YOZORA]
Not good enough.
I'll never forgive you for that!
Die!
I am the demon Astaro!
What the--?
You will never
escape me now, Kodaka!
Please forgive me!
Yozora!
It's all over.
Are you okay?
So weird.
I forgot.
You only left me there
for five minutes.
It felt like so much longer.
Rika owes you an apology.
She lied when she said
it was a time machine.
It's not.
It's actually a kind of sleep
aide that Rika created to give
a hypnotic effect to the sleeper
so they could dream about
whatever they wanted simply by
wishing hard enough for it.
So wait.
That was just a dream?
Rika only wanted to pull
a little prank on you,
but it sounded like
she ended up giving you
a terrible nightmare instead.
She is very sorry
for her actions.
Hey, don't be.
I'm sorry for criticizing
your inventions.
It was never my place.
That time machine's brilliant!
You should be proud!
Sure, things got
weird at the end,
but I really did feel like
I was time travelling!
It was so awesome!
[KODAKA] Most of all,
you allowed me to tell her
what I didn't before,
even if it was all a dream.
Rika is happy.
That means you did get
to time travel with dreams
as your portal.
[KODAKA]
Yeah.
I went back ten years.
Oh.
Are you sure it
was that far back?
Okay, hold on.
I have a question for you.
Yeah?
Shoot.
Why were you talking
to Yozora in that dream?
I mean, if you
went back ten years?
Hey, Taka, isn't this cool?
We get to do the
preview this time.
Things got weird ten years
into our future, didn't they?
I wonder what'll happen next?
Well, we say the title
of the next episode.
Unbreakable Strange Girl.
That sounds awful.
Couldn't they come up with
something more appealing?
I wonder which girl they think
is unbreakable and strange?
I'm guessing you.
I've never done a strange
thing in my whole life!
I think dressing like
a boy and picking on people
for no reason
counts as 'strange.'
That was way harsh, Taka.