-So last weekend...
-Yeah?
We went swimming
together,
and that was fun,
but like...
I just don't know
what it meant, you know?
Yeah.
I'm sorry I'm late!
Do you wanna go
there together?
Yeah. Next Sunday
sound good to you?
The season of happy kids.
Awesome.
I'm back.
It's so hot outside.
What's wrong,
Guernica?
-Fight back!
-Raysis, why?!
Um... Why don't you have
the air conditioner on?
I think it broke.
Of course you don't!
You've never been anything
more than a fool!
[Music]
Okay, I'm back yet again.
Did you get us a new AC?
Yeah, but they won't
be able to install it
for three more days.
Oh no... Three whole days...
Is there anything more
worthless than, humans...
Fascinating...
All right then, for the
time being at least...
Let us go forth
and make merry
with our usual
purgatorial feast.
I am still Rasis Vi
Felicity Sumeragi, right?
Even if I were to be
surrounded with flames
measuring twenty
million degrees...
I would remain the great and
mighty King of all the night.
Why don't you change in
a shorts or something?
This dress embodies my powers
of darkness, stupid head!
I can't just take it
off because I'm hot!
Yeah, right...
You want some tea?
Is this episode new?
Oh, it's the one you
recorded yesterday.
Here you go.
You've backed
me into a corner.
Who would believe it?
Now... Gaze upon
my true form!
Releasing binding spell!
Unleashing magic power!
Yes... This is my true form.
True form...
But it's so beautiful!
I guess the finale
must be next week.
Brother!
I'm releasing the...
Binding Spell!
I mean, releasing...
Binding spell!!
Why aren't you
watching me?!
Put everything you just
took off into the washer.
Okay.
Unleashing Magic Power!
Now, you may gaze
upon my true form.
-Ripoff?
-It's not a ripoff!
I did not desire for
it to be necessary
to unleash my true
power onto you.
Blame it on a particularly
annoying season of hell.
I do only what I must.
Sure thing,
whatever you say.
Hey... So listen...
I'm about to head
out to the club.
You wanna go with?
I mean, if you're allowed
to go out wearing that...
They do have a working
air conditioner.
I'll go.
-Hey Kobato...
-Yeah?
Those are clothes you wore in
elementary school, aren't they?
I can't believe you
still fit into them
even though you're in your
second year of middle school.
I wonder if you've
stopped growing already.
So what do
I do about it?
I don't wanna be
this little forever!
Wait, now that I'm
thinking about it...
As a member of
the Night Tribe,
I'm supposed
to be eternal...
Which means, of course...
My body will never get
discrepant or ugly with age.
That's a good point.
I'm glad you're not
gonna get discrepant.
You know...
Or decrepit...
It's whatever.
-Hey, we're here.
-You're late.
We're glad you made it
nonetheless, Big Brother...
-Hey! Big Brother!
-Come on in.
Long time no see, huh?
Long like forever, right?
Yukimura got me
sushi for lunch today.
How great is that?
And yesterday he
gave me steak.
He's the best, isn't
he, big brother?
Sushi... Steak?
Since you ordered
me to make sure
I only gave Miss Maria
food that tasted good.
Whatever I made for her,
I prepared with every bit
of my heart and soul.
Yeah, I know I said
that, but I mean...
Aren't you going
a bit overboard?
When you force fed me
that nasty medicine,
I swore I was gonna chop
something important
off of that she-male,
but now that you're not
crazy, it's different!
Thanks so much, Yukimura!
You should thank
Big Brother, not me.
Thank you, Big Brother.
I love you so, much!
You stupid!
Who do you think you are?
I hope you turn into a pig
from everything you eat,
so then my brother will hate
you and your nasty, fat guts!
Hey! What was that?!
Who the hell are you?
I'm my big brother's
little sister, thank you!
Cute! Hey Kobato!
You're that dummy vampire?!
The one that tricked me?
Incarnation of darkness!
Begone! Begone!
She bit me!
Why would you do that!
Dummy stupid-headed
dummy-head!
Of course she bit you...
That's what vampires do.
That's what you get,
Tool of God!
And now that you've been
bitten by a real vampire,
your cursed fate shall be to
become a vampire as well!
Is that true, Big Brother?
That is normally how
these things work, yeah.
Nooooo...!
I'm gonna turn
into a vampire.
I don't wanna turn
Maria... I've heard if you
bathe in the suns rays
immediately after
getting bitten...
It kills the curse and you
won't turn into a vampire.
-What, are you serious?
-Of course I am.
Although it won't work
if you wear clothes.
You have to be completely
and utterly naked.
Okay, got it!
Thank you, Yozora!
You are really evil.
She's just so stupid;
I can't help myself.
What do you want?
And please stop staring
at me; it's weird.
Kobato, you are just
the cutest thing...
But... what happened
to your goth-lolli look?
I liked it!
I just unleashed my true
power; no big deal.
I have no idea
what that means,
but I cannot stand
how adorable you are!
I wanna eat you alive
whenever I see you!
Please... Don't do that.
Tell Rika something.
What kind of panties
are you wearing?
You guys need
to cut it out.
Just take them off
so we can see them.
As God as my witness,
I'm gonna conquer
that cutey Kobato, too!
Behave yourself,
perverts.
You're freaking her out.
Shine on me!
The suns rays!
God's light
will save me!
The sucky thing about summer
is there's nothing to do.
Yeah.
At this point,
I would be okay
with ten times the amount
of summer homework
they forced on us.
Well, speak for yourself.
While we're sitting here
being bored to death,
I wonder what other
people have decided
to do with their free time.
They're having fun with
their friends, obviously.
I wish all the happy
people would just die.
I wish they'd die, too.
What'd video game
characters ever do to you?
In this scene, if I were
the writer of this game.
I'd so put in a killer shark.
A shark?
What're you being
all nasty for?
Come on, Meat.
If a shark appeared
out of nowhere
and tore apart all
those lame bimbos,
that would be an awesome
god game, and you know it.
Except that doesn't
make sense here,
so it would never happen...
They're at a public pool,
not in the freaking ocean.
A shark!
Ha... There's no way that's
a real shark, you guys.
Like, yeah...
It's gotta be a
radio controlled one
or something normal
like that...
Watch... no way this game
pulls something that cliché.
What is a real shark
doing in a public pool?
This is so lame!
Breathe...
Now, it's a comedy
so we should wait for the
punch line of the joke.
I can totally see how a
shark in a public pool
would set up
a good laugh...
I predict the lead character
ends up killing the shark
in some hilarious way...
I bet that'll make
my score go up!
No!! Mizuki!!!!!
You're right;
that was hilarious.
I've had enough of
this shitty game!
The name of that
game is called
Saint Jaws Academy
Tale, right?
Yeah, what of it?
Rika heard the ending of it was
supposed to be really bad...
Troll bad...
If you don't set up
flags on Saint Jaws...
It not only throws you
into a crappy ending...
But then it finishes
with a nasty gore scene
that practically
comes out of nowhere.
It's like, so random...
Actually, the game is kind
of famous for being stupid.
I had no idea chick
games could be so deep.
It's funny because I'd kill
to go to a pool right now.
What? You're saying
this immediately
after seeing a bunch
of oversexed heroines
devoured by a shark
at a public pool?
Does this mean you have a
death wish-please say yes.
Are you trying
to make sense?
Going swimming has nothing
to do with that game...
I'd just really like
to go to a pool, okay?
Oh, good.
I was getting worried.
Just know if you
ever decide
your fate is to be ripped
to shreds by a shark
I'll think about saving
you for at least a second...
So, you're welcome.
Uh... Okay, thank you?
Me too...
I wanna go to a pool.
Kobato! You can go
with me if you want!
We'll have the most
amazing time together!
Creepy Meat returns.
A pool, huh...?
Isn't that where
happy people go?
If I'd made some
friends yet...
I bet I'd wanna
go to a pool too.
It shouldn't be that hard
of a decision for you.
I've been to Sea God's Palace
Land before with Ko...
h... Hey! Why don't we
all go there together...
You know as a club
activity or something...
Call it a rehearsal
for the real thing.
That doesn't
suck too hard.
I mean it's not like we
have anything better to do.
-Let's go!
-Hey, Kodaka...
Try not to get too excited when
you see Rika in her swimsuit.
I bet you wear
a dress thing...
You know, like
those cover ups
that keep people from
seeing you in a suit.
What? No, I don't...
To prove it...
Rika will purchase
a sexy new suit,
which is bound to make
you drool all over her.
Low cut leg...
String bikini...
A barely there number...
a Band-Aid Piece...
Or nude!
For the win!
I have no idea what
half of those are...
Guess she's excited.
Hey sexy!
We're all over here!
You guys're
always early.
No we're not;
you're just late.
What's the deal; we weren't
supposed to meet here.
Holy crap!
It was like this
when we got here.
I bet they're all headed
to the pool, too.
I can't believe how
awful this crowd is.
Hey, Yozora, are you
feeling okay...?
You look kinda sick.
I am...
It's not from
the bus...
It's from all the people.
I feel real bad...
-Here.
-I'm good...
I'm not gonna
throw up.
Definitely not
gonna throw up...
Definitely.
Rika's not gonna
hurl, either.
-You feel sick, too?
-Yep...
Rika's no good
in crowds.
They make her
real anxious...
But don't worry...
Rika's fine...
If she must...
she can easily find
energy from you...
As in from
below the belt!
Wow... That's great.
By the way...
When Yozora says,
"Definitely not gonna throw up."
Is it kind of a turn on,
or is that just Rika?
No, it's absolutely
just Rika...
Are you only
sick mentally?
So, Kobato...
Whatcha wanna do when
we get to the pool?
Go swim.
I guess that's obvious.
Would you like for me to
teach you how to swim?
No... I know how.
Of course you do...
What are you good at?
-Long distance.
-Cool...
Why don't we do
that together?!!
No.
She's even adorable
when she's being rude!
I know she's sweet
on the inside, though!
Oh no...
Are you okay?
Bro, a little
help here, please!
-I don't like this at all.
-Did you hurt yourself?
Oh... I'm so sorry.
I wonder if
they're sisters;
they're a lot alike.
We finally made it.
Yeah.
Hooray.
You see, I told
you I was fine.
I so did not throw up.
Yeah. Way to go.
Yozora definitely
did not hurl.
Wow, there are so
many people here.
It wasn't like this
last time, at all.
I guess it's so hot
even commoners will cough up
some money to go to the pool.
Curse this damn
infertile sun!
Luckily, I exist
in my true form now,
so its rays can no
longer destroy me.
Can we go in...
I'm so hot.
Look at that...
No wonder it's so
freakin' crowded.
We're risking our
lives being here.
Why did we not
do this in July?
Look on the bright side;
at least it's cheaper.
Who cares?! I'd rather pay
twice as much than be forced
to deal with
these people.
I think their half-price
sale can totally suck it.
Well, speak for
yourself again...
Come on, let's go.
That took forever...
-Here.
-Thanks!
Shall we change and meet
in front of the showers?
Yeah.
A girl!
Look at that...
I guess I'm just
one of those girls
who's instantly
hated by all guys
even though
I'm really a boy.
No... You're wrong.
That's not true.
Hey... He might
not look like it,
but this dude
is totally a...
guuyyy!
Wait... I Um...
Yeah you tell 'em, bro!
This should be fine.
I guess we should
get changed.
Yes, that sounds good.
Why the hell did you bring
a girl's swimsuit with you?
Because Yozora told me to;
she said that I should
wear one today.
And why would you ever
ask Yozora for advice?
Because Yozora has become
my trusted advisor.
She had a good point.
I want my inner masculinity
to shine through
even when wearing
women's clothing...
I thought this would be
a good challenge for me.
Way too intense.
Well, I did bring along
a man's swimsuit too,
just in case.
Dude... What's that?
Oh... It's a loincloth.
By all means, challenge yourself
with the women's swimsuit.
I'll let you borrow the
loincloth if you want to.
I don't; thanks, though.
Are you doing okay...?
Do you need me to help
you get into your suit?
No!
All right...
You need some help?
Yes.
I'd appreciate it.
Calm down, Kodaka...
He's a dude.
All set.
That was very nice...
Thank you.
Yeah...
How do girls put
stuff like that on
and take it off
all by themselves?
-Hey!
-Is anything wrong?
Are you okay?
Why... are you
hiding your chest?
Because it's not
very muscular,
and I'm embarrassed by it.
But if ...
If you really want to
see it, I'll let you.
I don't wanna see...!
Just put your top
back on already.
Understood, sir.
It's about time; what
took you guys so long?!
Nothing... More importantly,
I'd rather not
talk about it.
Why is Yukimura wearing
a girl's swimsuit?
I said I'd rather
not talk about it...
Hey, wait...
Where are Yozora and Rika?
They told me they'd be out
after they rested a bit.
Yeah, it looked like
that ride was pretty
rough on both of them.
I'm gonna go swim now.
Yay! You guys it's so cold!
Hurry up, bro!
Coming!
Crazy.
Having this many people
cannot be legal.
Long distance is out.
Yeah, I can imagine
that would be difficult.
This is gross...
And annoying.
I wish that shark
would show up.
But I thought sharks
were too cliché for you.
When the girls
finally get out.
How about we head
down to the lazy river
and maybe the
water slide?
Fine... This is awful.
That it is.
It wasn't this bad
last time we came.
No...
It was way better.
Yeah, way better until
you got all mad at me.
What are you
talking about?
-You got mad at me!
-No.
You were pissed.
But then, when we
were leaving...
What did you say
"thank you" for?
What's going on?!
Those girls are taking
for freaking ever!
Guess so.
I'll be right back...
I'm gonna go
check on them.
I wonder what she's
upset about now.
I get it...
At the time, there
were only three of us
in the Neighbors Club...
We've got more
members now...
Show me.
I guess we haven't exactly
made any friends yet, either.
But, depending on
how you look at it,
I think we've all at
least changed a lot.
Kodaka!
Yozora just sent
me this message.
They went home?!
Kodaka!
Where'd he go?
Yozora! Rika!
You guys...
Don't go!
Come on!
Wait!
She's so stupid.
Why'd they have to leave;
I had planned to show off
my ultra elegant
swimming form to her.
Or maybe we haven't
changed after all.
What'd you say?
What? Nothing.
Should we go home, too?
Yeah.
The Neighbors Club
activity report...
Today's activity...
Nothing.
[Music]
-Here's some shabushabu.
-Meat! Meat! Meat!.
-Also some sushi...
-Raw meat! Raw meat! Raw meat!
I made you steak, too.
It's marbled and delicious!
-Broiled eel over rice.
-I can't even see the rice;
there's so much meat!
This is too yummy;
I can't stop eating!
Thank you!
I can't move anymore.
Oh no... I just had the
worstest most scariestest dream
I've ever had in
my whole life.
Next... The President's
Recollections are painful.
I'm never gonna eat again!