Thank you!
What are you thanking us for?
Kobato's birthday
party yesterday.
I appreciate everything
you guys did for her.
And I dunno, it made me feel
good to know you care enough
to go through
all that trouble.
So thank you.
You guys are awesome.
Whatever.
There's no need to get
all emotional about it.
Huh?
That wasn't emotional.
I just said thanks!
Regardless, the fact is
the party was great.
There are people all over this
world who don't have friends
to help them out
when they need it.
So, thank you, Kodaka for
reminding us every day should be
a celebration of friends!
[KODAKA]
Yeah!
We could've been cutting our own
cake and singing to ourselves
on our birthdays, ya know?
But we don't frickin' have to!
It's not like I really need
a reason to celebrate, though.
Kudos, Big Brother.
[KODAKA]
Rika?
What's the matter with you?
Rika was just thinking about how
excited she is to be working on
the school festival!
She thinks we
should stay focused!
Yeah, I guess you're right.
That sounds like a good plan.
[KODAKA]
No, it doesn't.
I'd rather hang out and
talk about friendship.
But I get what Rika's trying
to say without quite saying it.
And she's totally right.
We're here.
Sup?
No freaking way!
Kobato is the
sweetest thing ever!
I could just eat you up
on a bed of rice!
[YOZORA] Is a cat café where
you dress like cats?
Have you really
never heard of one?
It's literally a café with
cats running around while
you drink tea and kick it.
[YOZORA]
No way!
For a town as
depressing as this,
that's actually pretty awesome.
Do whatever you want.
I'm out.
I've got my hands
full for the festival.
Oh that's right.
I forgot you said you were doing
something with your class.
"History of Toya," wasn't it?
[SENA]
Right!
I suggested we do the history of
the Almighty Goddess Sena
Kashiwazaki, but all it did was
remind the other girls
in the class how pitiful
their lives were
so they said no.
Just thinking about it
makes me want to hit someone
in their kneecaps.
[YOZORA] Well if our resident
idiot is out, then there's
no point of doing a comedy
routine, is there?
That's too bad.
Next!
Whoa!
Just because Sena's
not helping doesn't mean
it's not a good option!
It was the worst option.
Rika agrees.
We're not that funny.
It would have been
quite inappropriate.
My sources say
the choice was correct.
Fine.
I get it.
It's done.
Kobato, you're here.
So does this mean you're
skipping the middle school
festival today to be with us?
Did your exhibit suck?
What were you going to do?
[KODAKA]
Yeah, tell us--for inspiration.
Uh.
Most Foolish Kindred.
My many secrets shall
never be known to you.
I guess that means
I don't have to cook
any more pork flavored ramen.
Do you dare threaten the great
Raysis Vi Felicity Sumeragi,
ruler of the
majestic night and sky?
Foolish Mortal.
I guess I get all the leftover
meatloaf tonight, too.
[KOBATO]
Hey!
That's not fair!
Yes, it is.
Tell me and you can eat.
Fine.
It's a movie.
Like a real life film?
That sounds like so much fun!
That might work.
So what are you doing?
Acting?
Directing?
What?
That is of no concern to you.
Cool.
I guess you don't mind
being cut off from gaming.
[KOBATO]
I'm the lead.
[KODAKA]
Huh?
You're what?
[KOBATO]
I'm acting.
You're laughing?
For the third time, I'm acting!
I'm the cocka-doodie Lead, okay?
The movie is about me!
[EVERYONE]
You're the lead?
That's amazing!
Congratulations!
I so wanna see that movie!
Say you'll take me!
Okay, one thing at a time.
Kobato, if you're the lead,
why are you here?
Don't they need you?
[KODAKA]
Oh no.
You ditched them?
Listen to me.
Being picked as
the lead's an honor.
You can't let them down.
There are so many kids who
never get chosen to do anything
in class all year long--
much less be labeled the best.
Not even to be the line-leader?
[KODAKA]
Nope.
See?
You're lucky
to have that chance.
So be a rock star
and make the best of it.
Isn't it cool to know there are
so many people in your class
who need your
awesomeness to succeed?
Yeah it is!
Just wait until they see what
my Raysis Vi Felicity Sumeragi--
ruler of the night can do!
Bye!
I shall be leaving you now!
Break your legs and
arms out there, okay?
I bet we could make an even
better movie for the festival.
Rika figured you were
going to suggest that.
No objection here.
I think it's a great idea!
You already have your star.
Obvs.
Yeah, I'm fine with a movie.
Sounds like a
majority, it's official!
Question?
Yeah?
Whaddya got, Rika?
Rika is a fan of filmmaking,
but she wants to know
what the plot will be.
Don't worry about that.
I've got it covered!
What do you mean
you have it covered?
If you're thinking of writing
the whole thing without us,
it's going to be crap
and you know it!
Yeah, I can't understand
a word of that squawking but
I'm guessing you don't
trust my creativity?
[SENA]
What creativity?
Come on, Yozora.
You know you don't have the
greatest story-writing resume.
I hear what you're saying,
and I'm prepared to
learn from my mistakes.
If you have any ideas about the
plot, I'm willing to listen,
so dry your eyes.
Let's do this.
Who has a suggestion?
I'll write it down
and we can vote.
Maybe this time
nobody has to get raped.
[YOZORA]
But what if it's tasteful?
[KODAKA] Not the reaction
I was expecting.
[SENA]
You crushed her dreams.
Tadaa!
I has arrived, Poopy Faces!
Consider your day made;
and you are welcome!
That means everyone's
here so we can get started.
So should we just tell you
our ideas or do you
want us to write them down?
[YOZORA]
No, I'll write them up here
on the board so we
can see them and compare.
How 'bout this?
A transfer student comes to a
new country and everyone picks
on him because of his accent
but later, they discover
he's pretty cool and he becomes
the most popular guy in class.
Um, the lead has to be a girl.
I require a juicy role.
I require a giant juicy
steak with French fries!
I don't care what the plot is,
but I'd really like
to play a samurai.
Rika thinks the boy student
should meet another cute boy
at school and have
a steamy love scene.
[KODAKA] Is there a way to make
all that work together?
Let me just sleep on it tonight
and then I can start spinning it
all into gold.
It'll be the best
script you ever read.
[PHONE]
You've got mail.
[KODAKA] Why are you
messaging me this late?
All that to ask if I want
to go to a movie with her.
But it makes sense
to watch an actual movie
before we make our own.
Maybe we'll get some ideas.
So tomorrow we'll just have the
club meeting at the theater.
Assuming c-u-z means 'because'.
Don't tell the others, huh?
Okay.
Understood.
Send!
Where are you?
[YOZORA]
Kodaka!
[KODAKA]
Are we going to a movie or
do you have plans to assassinate
someone in that ninja suit?
You think you're so funny.
Let's go.
So which movie are we
researching today?
I have no idea yet.
I figured I'd wait 'til
we got here then pick from
whatever's about to start.
Well, that's kinda random.
Hey, that's how
I always pick movies.
Don't judge me.
[YOZORA]
How about this one?
[KODAKA]
Um.
That looks horrifying.
I'm guessing no?
No, it looks great!
Why are we still standing here?
C'est bon!
[FRENCH MAN]
C'est si bon!
[FRENCH WOMAN]
C'est bon!
[FRENCH MAN]
Oui, C'est si si bon!
[FRENCH WOMAN]
C'est si bon!
[FRENCH MAN]
C'est bon!
[KODAKA]
Well, I learned a lot.
Oh shut up.
No you didn't!
If I'd known it was
going to be like that
I'd have never invited you!
[KODAKA]
Wasn't that bad.
So.
If it wasn't so bad, then does
that mean you might be open to
doing something similar for our
movie, like just for pretend?
What did you say?
I can't hear you.
[YOZORA]
Nothing!
I just said I'm thirsty!
Look there!
That is a beautiful sunset
that requires tea!
'Kay, but this place
serves tea, too.
Yeah but, I need a
different kind of tea from
a certain place, so.
Follow me.
Meow!
So cute!
Uh.
Did you just meow at them?
Aww!
[YOZORA]
No.
Nope.
Oh, there you go!
Good kitty, you caught it!
You really have to like cats
a lot to hang out in here.
[YOZORA] There's no
such thing as a person
who doesn't like cats.
I'm gonna file that
under 'debatable.'
[YOZORA] I'm gonna file
you under 'shut up.'
Don't you already have a cat
at home you can plank with?
[YOZORA]
Nope.
Our landlord won't allow it.
Besides, even if I could
I wouldn't want to get one.
Huh?
Really?
Why not?
Don't you remember
when we were little?
My cat, Night?
Come on, Night!
Hurry up!
Yay!
Good Night!
[YOUNG YOZORA]
Night?
[YOUNG KODAKA]
Come here, Night!
[YOUNG YOZORA]
Night?
Hey Night!
Come back, Night!
I don't think I'll ever
get over how hard it was
to lose Night like that.
Like, what's the point of
getting close to someone
or something if they're
just going to leave?
It's much easier to keep my
distance so it won't matter
when they're gone.
[YOZORA]
Thanks for coming with me today!
Prepare your mind to be
blown by an awesome script!
Can't wait!
[YOZORA]
This is kind of weird,
but hanging out sort of
made me feel like 'that' again.
[KODAKA]
Like what?
You know, friends like
we were ten years ago.
I know what you mean.
Like, comfortable.
It was familiar but sort of
felt like starting over.
[YOZORA]
Well good night!
See you tomorrow!
I bet you jerks thought
it couldn't be done!
It's pretty awesome
if I say so myself.
I have no doubt
you guys will agree.
The hardest part's done!
Now let's start filming!
Um, why are you
dressed like that?
How dare you speak to
Raysis Vi Whatever that way!
Shut up, that is so fake!
Hey, this is pretty good.
The dialogue is so intense!
I can't believe this actually
came out of you, Yozora!
I'm seriously impressed!
You're like
a genius or something!
Do you really like it?
I mean, well, duh.
[RIKA] Rika has decided
that this is our script.
Next thing we need
to do is cast it.
Actually the cast
is already set.
Obviously, I will
play our ingénue, Kuya.
Kuya's best friend and
transfer student, Hirotaka,
will be played by Kodaka.
Oh.
That's cool.
[YOZORA] Sana, the bitter,
jealous, yet questionably
popular girl will be played
by Meat, of course.
Yukimura will be Noboyoki.
The shy little boy who is
secretly in love with Hirotaka.
Okay.
[YOZORA] Then there's
Serika who's always playing
stupid pranks on Kuya
for being with Hirotaka.
Rika plays her.
Kuya's annoying little sister,
Mari is going to be Maria.
Rude.
[MARIA] Why does she
have to be annoying?
Well, is it perfect
or is it perfect?
[SENA]
None of the above!
What's the matter, Tits?
You don't like your role?
You gave yourself the lead!
And you made me the villain!
I didn't cast it until
I reread the script.
I just did what
made the most sense.
Sana is the popular
one--which means she should
be devastatingly good looking.
As much as I hate saying it,
you do fit the description.
Her past doesn't
make her the villain;
it makes her the more
relatable character.
You said you wanted
a juicy role, right?
Well it would be nice
to show my range.
Yeah, okay, I'm in.
Great.
All roles have been accepted.
Rika has a question!
[RIKA] Yes, Rika, you can wear
your hair any way you want.
It's not about hair this time!
If we're casting based on
looks and personality, then Rika
has to say that Kodaka as the
stud transfer student is not
the best choice.
Me?
But why not?
[RIKA] Hirotaka's personality
doesn't seem to work.
He's honorable; he has a passion
for justice; he's courageous;
he's totally popular.
He's supposed to be funny and
sociable and charming, right?
You have him written as tall and
athletic with rugged features.
[KODAKA]
It's like we're twins.
Nothing about this guy
sounds anything like Kodaka!
No one would ever believe it!
I didn't think it
would be that noticeable.
Wait, what's that noticeable?
I was thinking the same thing.
You couldn't do
a worse casting job.
The real Hirotaka
would be offended.
If Big Brother wasn't puny
he might look like a cool guy.
Is there another reason?
Why would anyone choose
Kodaka as a leading man type?
Yeah, there is, actually.
It's not about the look.
It's 'cause Kodaka and I
have known each other
since we were kids.
That's right.
I almost forgot about that.
Kuya and Hirotaka were
childhood friends so I chose
my actual childhood friend to
play opposite me in the film.
I figured it would be
more realistic for us both.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
[SENA]
No.
Maybe a dressing room
with candy.
[RIKA] Let me get this straight,
if you don't play Kuya then we
don't have to cast your actual
friend as the lead, right?
In fact, we may not even
need that character at all?
What are you
trying to say, Rika?
[RIKA] It's just that
maybe we should all vote
on the cast instead.
[SENA]
I can get behind that.
Hey, nobody's talking to you!
What's the matter?
Are you worried that
we won't vote for you
as Kuya or something?
Of course I'm not.
I know you guys want
this movie to be good, too.
Okay, all the votes are tallied
and this is what we've got.
If I'm playing Kuya,
that means I'm the lead?
This is so ridiculous.
Yay!
I get to be the bitter, bossy,
booby, popular, pretty girl!
Yup.
That is awkward.
Nobuyuki?
So Rika's playing a young boy?
[KODAKA]
What the crap?
You've got to be kidding me?
How did I go from the male lead
to playing the little sister?
This is your fault, isn't it?
[SENA] Geez, it's not
like I had a choice.
Plus, I thought you
might enjoy a challenge.
Well, you're wrong.
And what do you mean
you didn't have a choice?
Uh.
Can we discuss why
you're yelling at me?
I'm not the only one who voted!
Who else voted for me, then?
Me!
What?
Why?
Because it looks like fun.
You're Big Brother every day!
I wanted to see you
be someone different.
Doesn't get any more
non-brother than being a sister!
[RIKA] Rika thinks there may
have been ulterior motives
for voting the way we did.
At least no one can
accuse us of typecasting.
[KODAKA] Yeah, I don't know that
this is what we're going for.
Shouldn't we take another vote?
I mean it's gonna be fine.
You'll make an
amazing lead, Yukimura.
Thank you!
I promise to
make you proud, sir!
Of course you will.
I just need to figure out
how to get into my role.
I guess I'll change it
to a little brother.
It's not going to hurt the
story if we switch genders.
Now what?
Do you want to
play a little boy?
Uh.
No, I just feel kinda bad.
Huh?
Well, you wrote
the whole script,
and I just made
even more work for you.
Hold on, I feel like
you're showing signs of having
a soul and it's
creeping me out a bit.
[SENA]
Rude dot com!
I-- I just liked
your script, okay?
It's pretty awesome.
Thank you.
I mean it's not a big deal to
change a sister to a brother.
The script's
basically the same.
Oh.
You sure?
Well then I guess it's fine.
[KODAKA]
What the hell is happening?
This is a completely
different story now!
Why?
It's still the same.
Um, no it is not!
[SENA] Who the heck is
this Kotaro guy?
[YOZORA]
Kuya's little brother.
I know!
But why are
they suddenly twins?
Mari was never a twin?
Why now?
What are you trying to pull?
This is not what
I signed up for!
A little suspicious how he
went from a side character
to pretty much the new lead.
This was supposed to be about
Kuya and Hirotaka's friendship,
but now you have them
hating each other.
Yeah, because they were never
that close to begin with.
I just forgot
to write it in, okay?
But you said they
were best friends!
No, Hirotaka just thought
of Kuya as a friend
of a best friend.
He knew her, but that's
about as far as it went.
She was actually friends
with Kotaro who was friends
with Hirotaka so
they all hung out together.
That sounds like
a lot to keep up with.
What's wrong with letting
all three of them be friends?
Because 'friend of a friend'
does not mean friend.
It just means acquaintances.
Besides, I don't want to write
about a three-way friendship.
It's too hard.
It's two friends
and their friend.
I guess I kind of
understand what you mean.
[SENA]
That doesn't make sense!
Why not keep Kuya and Hirotaka
best friends and make Kotaro
the odd one out since
he's the new character?
That way you don't
have to change the story!
Sorry, it won't work.
[SENA]
Why not?
Because it's much more
natural for him to get along
with Kotaro.
I mean, since that's who
Kodaka is gonna be playing.
I get it now.
You just want Kodaka
to play whoever your
friend is in the film.
Yeah.
It makes sense that way.
No, it doesn't!
You're just recreating the past
instead of telling a story!
[YOZORA]
What did you say to me?
Well?
What past am I recreating?
Uh.
The past of you and
Kodaka being close friends.
That shouldn't matter now.
You should be trying
to tell a new original story.
Not using this movie as a way
to try to turn back time.
How dare you?
That isn't true.
Stop being so dramatic!
You're the only one
being dramatic and obsessing
about the past!
Quit trying so hard
to hold on to it.
You're dragging everyone else
down with you and it's not fair!
Yozora, you okay?
[YOZORA]
It's your fault.
If you weren't here I wouldn't
have to feel like this.
It's your fault.
Jerk.
You just wait.
Someday you're gonna know
exactly how this feels!
[KODAKA]
Yozora! Come back!
[SENA] I didn't mean
for that to happen.
I'm sorry.
This sucks.
Maybe I shouldn't
have been so honest.
I was only trying
to get through to her.
Why can't she let the past go?
[KODAKA]
Yozora!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I forgot my bag in
gym class today, that's all.
Sucks when that happens.
[YOZORA]
What do you think?
Should Hirotaka be best
friends with Kuya or Kotaro?
Be honest.
It makes no difference to me.
I just want the
story to be good.
[YOZORA]
I know.
I just-- I want it to be you.
Huh?
I didn't quite catch that.
Tell me which is more important
to you--our friendship the way
it was ten years ago
or the way it is now?
I don't know how to answer that.
They're both different!
If they're so different then you
should have a preference, right?
I guess I need inspiration.
What's your pick?
Would you go back to ten
years ago or are you happy
with the way things are?
Um.
Well that's a no-brainer for me.
I'd go back ten years.
Does that mean the present
isn't as important?
[YOZORA]
It's hard to explain.
[KODAKA]
I know what you mean.
[YOZORA]
Yeah.
I totes love it!
You really shouldn't
be shocked by my ability
to make adjustments.
Rika is so excited and relieved.
This story is ten
thousand times better than
the last one you wrote!
Good job!
Rika was worried you
were going to change Kotaro.
Thank goodness you didn't.
It's perfect this way!
It's obvious you worked
very hard on this.
Thank you.
Thank you for your feedback.
Okay, well if no one else
has any other questions
I say we get moving!
I'm ready to film this thing.
How about you?
[KODAKA]
We're gonna rule!
[YUKIMURA]
I hope I do your story justice.
[SENA] This movie has no
choice but to be the best
because I'm in it!
[YOZORA]
Shut up, Titszilla.
[MARIA] This story sounds
familiar for some reason.
Dear mademoiselle Yozora,
you look so very sad
and alone over there.
Poor thing.
I was happy that she was able
to explore and learn more
about our love story.
We hope we helped.
But fair is fair, my sweet.
Next time, share the secrets
of your heart or bedroom!
Now to sleep, my Stephanie.
Je t'aime always.
Oh Dear Jonathon!
A million times, Je t'aime!
Please, join us next time
for Stray Cats Over Heat!
Wait just a minute.
My loins are over heating!
C'est si bon!