-This is some view up here.
-Yeah.
As long as you
and I are friends,
then as far as I'm concerned,
I don't need anyone else.
I'll always be here
by your side...
Even if the whole world
turns its back on you.
Don't say things like that,
it's so embarrassing.
Hey.
I think you should
have a nick name...
What do you want
me to call you?
A nick name huh...?
What about Sora?
You should call me...
Taka.
You're so slow, Taka!
No fair, wait up!
Another dream?
You're such a slow poke!
No, I'm not...
I'm fast.
So weird...
I can't remember.
[Music]
Only one more week of
summer vacation left.
But I've been
a good student,
and I'm almost done with
all of my prep work.
I forgot to tell you.
I heard about a summer festival
that is starting tomorrow
at the shrine near the
Tooya shopping district.
A festival, huh?
And... Is that all?
I don't understand.
Is there a reason
you're telling us that?
Well. I'm pretty sure I saw
a flyer hanging somewhere
on my way to school yesterday
and I didn't know if any
of you guys had heard yet.
Thanks for passing
that info on...
I guess I was hoping
you were gonna suggest
we all go to the
festival together.
Why in the world would
I ever waste my time
going to a stupid,
over-crowded event like that?
Rika's with you there.
A couple of years ago,
Rika decided to go to the
biannual anime festival in Tokyo
thinking it might
be a lotta fun,
but boy was she wrong...
The train was so
cramped with people,
Rika could barely move.
She got off at the halfway
point and went home.
Rika learned her lesson:
no more festivals.
I've actually heard
of that festival...
People say it's
ridiculously crowded
because it's the only place
you can buy these exotic,
special edition books.
As big a fan as you are,
I'm surprised you
didn't stick it out.
Are you questioning
Rika's fandom right now?
That really chaps her hide!
And making a
girl's hide chapped
is not a very
gentlemanly thing to do!
There's no need to drag this
conversation into the gutter!
Do you know who
you're speaking to?
Without the gutter,
Rika has nothing left!
You could talk about science
or all your inventions.
Or how you're a cool girl
with awesome glasses.
You really should give
yourself more credit.
Rika needs her glasses
to learn science
so she can sell
her inventions
in order to pay for her
expensive smut habit!
This is who
Rika really is!
Besides, Rika has plenty of
contacts in the anime world
because of her
scientific capabilities,
so she gets special edition
volumes whenever she wants.
In fact, the only reason
she works with these
companies in the first place
is for all the
free cartoon porn!
I'll never doubt
your fandom again,
I can tell you
that much for sure.
Told you.
Uh... Hey, Kodaka?
At these festivals,
do they sell food...?
'Cause... if they have Octopus
Dumpling booths, I'm in!
I'm not sure
about Octopus,
but there's plenty
to eat there.
Wait, do you actually
like Octopus Dumplings?
Why...? You don't?
I do... Those dumplings
are my favorite.
Way back... When I was
a little kid in Osaka,
I didn't really fit in
with the people around me,
and I guess you could say
I was a bit depressed.
But my Dad used to bring me
home these Octopus dumplings
from this famous store.
And it became
my comfort food.
They say, "Octopus
dumplings every day,
keeps the depression away."
They're great...
Although. I can't
stomach those bastards
who sell crappy octopus
dumplings with a straight face!
Hey... Calm down,
it's just food...!
I agree they're super yummy,
but it's not worth working
yourself into a frenzy over.
They taste really good,
let's just leave
it at that, okay?
I love them so much,
if you want to buy me
some as a present,
I would totally let you.
Do you really want me to
get you Octopus dumplings?
Dumplings rule!
Big bro...! If she gets them,
then I get them too!
Looks like it's a
done deal then...
We're going to
the summer festival.
Yeah!
Octopus is probably
against your religion...
Maybe you should
stay home, freak!
Big bro and I are going alone,
you vampire scum...!
You should stay home...
-Don't ruin our date!
-Me too...
I wanna go...
Yeah...! Dumplings
would hit the spot!
Same here...
I'd like to come, if
that's all right with you.
Of course.
So... That brings our group to
five people total... How fun!
-Hold on a second!
-Just hold your horses!
I'm not gonna be the
only one to miss out!
Guess that makes
it seven...
I thought you two
didn't like crowds.
We like Octopus dumplings!
All right...
Now that's a commitment to
food if I've ever seen it.
Kodaka, we're over here!
Hey...! Here early as usual.
Rika?
Look what you can do when
you put your mind to it.
Is that some kind of
back handed compliment?!
If you're gonna
be insulting,
just come out with it!
I think you look
really nice.
Thank you very much,
that's such a lovely
thing for you to say.
You're going to
make Rika blush.
I guess I can't win
with you, can I?
Since we're just
missing Meat
there's no point
in waiting around...
Let's move out, she'll
have to catch up to us.
Trying to leave me
behind, are you?
You're so rude!
That figures. Never can be
too careful around you...
Well, I'm here now,
so let's get this party
started, shall we?
What the heck was that for?
Don't worry about it...
Come on guys, let's go!
Hey...! Wait for us!
What's the matter
with you, Kodaka...?
It's tradition for girls to wear
Yukatas to summer festivals.
So why didn't you
make Kobato wear one?
It's not like she's
required to wear a Yukata;
I mean look at Yozora;
she didn't wear hers.
Please, let's not bring
commoners into this...
Listen: I wanna
see Kobato wearing
one of those
robes right now!
I hate to disappoint you
but Kobato doesn't
own a Yukata.
Kodaka!
Rika has good news:
there's a shop right here
where you guys can purchase
whatever you need.
That's perfect!
You wanna wear a Yukata
just like the rest
of us girls don't you?
What do you say we give
it a shot and try some on?
Kay.
Let's make it quick though,
I'm hungry for octopus.
I hope you have to spend
the rest of eternity in there
and never get to eat!
Oh yeah...?!
Eat this, bloodsucker!
They'll never give up.
Yukimura...
Go on ahead and
buy some dumplings
so we can avoid
all this drama.
That sounds like a plan...
And thanks for trusting
me to be your gopher;
I won't let you down.
You should probably
buy one too.
Thanks for the advice,
but I'm okay.
Your good looks are your only
redeeming quality, you know...?
You really should take
advantage of that.
Yeah... Sena's right...
A Yukata would
really compliment
your long, beautiful hair,
don't you think?
Uh.... No.
Thank you.
But that's not
really my style.
Too bad she won't wear one,
I bet she'd
look beautiful.
Big bro!
She's so cute.
She's just adorable...
Oh, I wanna gobble
her to pieces!
I think you look great.
She looks better
than great...
She's the cutest little
thing I've ever seen in my life
and you'd better
be nice to her
and tell her as much or else,
do you understand me?
You heard me tell you
I loved it, right?
But you on the
other hand...
You look completely
ridiculous
with your pudding colored hair
clashing with that robe.
My hair?
Specifically the color.
You're a laughing
stock at school.
Literally everyone
makes fun of you.
Maybe you should
try making it black.
Funny you should
mention that,
I've actually considered dyeing
it a different color before.
But the thing is, my mom's
hair looked just like this.
And she's gone.
Oh... Right.
You see... For the most part
I'm a spitting image of my Dad,
but the hair's
my Mom's...
Sometimes, I wish I
looked more like Kobato,
she's got her face, her hair
and basically
everything else too.
Since my hair is the only
thing I got from my mother
that you can tell
by looking at me,
it'd be way too difficult
to ever let it go.
Dyeing it another color
would feel like
turning my back on
where I came from,
and who I really am.
They can make fun of me...
But I like my hair,
'cause it always
makes me think of her.
That's so cool.
There's no question...
You're way different from
the other boys at school.
Come on...!
Let's go have fun!
Ready to go?
Hey... We've been
looking for you.
Sorry we're so late!
That's okay!
It's so good!
It's rude to talk
with your mouth full.
These Octopus
Dumplings are amazing!
You're so tiny, how
can you eat that much?
I think I've died and
gone to food heaven!
Huh...? Be lady-like,
that is no way to eat!
Rika's practicing her
erotic eating techniques
on this banana.
Are you getting turned on?
Not at all, no.
Here... Have some of mine...
-Ahh!
-No!
Something's not right.
Here you go.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh... That's okay.
For you.
Hey thanks a lot.
Let's see here...
I wonder how this
one will taste.
Well what do you think...?
Is it good?
It's got a light
fluffy texture,
but the thin skin ruins
the whole experience.
Plus there's not enough
Octopus meat inside.
It sucks.
This is all my fault.
Gross... Come on you guys,
let's all look for a better
octopus dumpling stand!
Count me out I think
I've had enough.
Rika feels the same.
Sounds great...!
I'm still hungry,
I wanna eat that thing
that looks like a cloud!
Thanks for buying
me all that food;
everything was awesome!
Yeah I'm completely
stuffed after that.
But hold on...
You guys...! You said
you wanted to eat
delicious octopus dumplings,
didn't you?!
If I eat more, I'll puke.
Then why the heck did we
come here in the first place?!
I think we've all had plenty
to eat, right everyone?
-Let's go home.
-Good idea.
No you can't leave yet!
You're not the boss
of us, okay Meat...?
Besides, what else is
there to do here?
No one's leaving
till I say so!
Yeah... you can't go...!
We're here, we might as well
stick around and play games!
If you wanna
scoop up goldfish
and throw rings like a little
child, you can be my guest!
Hey... I'm not a little kid,
I just like to have fun...
I was going to ask you
to compete against me
in a 'head to head' festival
gaming competition.
But since you're a chicken,
I won't waste my breath.
I already told you,
there's nothing I hate more than
being around a massive crowd.
But I'm not afraid
of you, Meat!
Besides... This place...?
Compared to how crazy the
pool was the other day
it's a piece of cake...
I think it's about time I give
you a little reality check,
what do you say?
Well, I suppose
I'll let you try...
So what game should
we play first...?
I'm an expert at
scooping gold fish.
What I mean to say is...
I challenge you to
a goldfish showdown!
I hate to break it to you,
but when it comes to goldfish,
I'm the queen of the pond!
Sorry to shatter
your delusion,
but the only thing you're
queen of is the morons...
Time to find out
who's number one!
Here's your money, sir.
Thanks...! Here ya go!
Thank you!
Go!
Hey, it tore...!
This is all a rip off!
Yeah, because it's
made outta paper...
The idea's to catch a
fish without tearing it.
Crap!
Come on... Just stop
moving so I can catch you,
you stupid little gold fish.
After I win, I'm gonna
make you pay me back
for all the money it'll
cost me to beat you
in this dumb competition!
I'll take ten more please.
Sure thing.
All right...!
That's cheating,
you can't do that!
I prefer to think of
it as 'sound strategy.'
I'm real sorry Miss,
but I don't allow
cheating at this booth...
Take a hike before
someone sees you,
and I can let you off
the hook this time.
Be thankful I
rescued you, fishy.
I've decided I'm gonna call
you 'Kandata' from now on...
You're lucky you made
it outta there alive.
Meat. We're gonna
do that next.
It doesn't matter
what we play,
because in the end
you're going down.
Try not cheating this time...!
Let's go!
-Okay, you're on!
-They're nuts...
Come on, why don't you
leave those two alone,
and come play some
games with us?
That's way too
simple, you idiot!
-Sounds fun!
-Awesome!
Yay! I'm gonna play
with my big bro!
Check it out, my water balloon's
way bigger than yours is!
Well, mine's a
whole lot prettier
so I guess I win,
you big stupid face!
Oh come on!
You seriously think you
beat me with that crap?!
Anyone with eyes could see
I dominated you back there!
Your umbrella looked
like a spaceship!
You're pathetic, Meat!
I'm not cut out for puny
detail work like that anyway!
Right there!
Let's settle this at
the roulette wheel!
Wait: sauce rice crackers?
Oh, fine!
Rika did good!
Wow... nice shot!
Okay...
Here. The special prize.
Hey, guess what...!
Rika already has
this gaming system,
so she's going to give
it to you as a present...
Please think of Rika
whenever you play it
and let her know if
she can help you out!
Wait... Why don't we
put it in the club room?
Yeah...
That sounds like
a good plan.
Boobs...!That
was a dirty trick!
Oh, shut up!
A win's a win,
don't be a sore loser!
How can you call
that a win, you jerk?!
Hey...! You two get
the hell outta here!
Take one.
Thanks a lot, Rika
really appreciates it.
There you are!
I've been looking
everywhere for you!
We're going to need
somebody to help
with all of
the stuff we won.
These stupid prizes are
really getting in the way
of our show down.
So we want you to carry
them... Right now.
No, I can't... I've
got my own things here.
What...? Is that
a game system?
But... How?
This is all courtesy
of 'bulls eye Rika.'
Neither of us
came out on top.
True... But if we would've kept
playing until the bitter end,
I feel confident
I would've won.
That's crap
and you know it!
Did you forget?
I'm ahead by one win, dummy!
Please, the gold fish
scoop doesn't count
because you cheated.
Let's go find Yukimura
and the girls.
I'll be waiting at the
west gate of the shrine.
So Stella said she was
cool to come get you?
But, because of all
the Festival traffic,
she told me
she doesn't know
how long it's gonna
take her to get here.
Oh.
Well, since we're
killing time,
why don't we go shoot
off some fireworks?
They have tons!
-For real?!!!
-Sounds like fun...
Besides, summer's almost over;
this could be our
only opportunity!
This is totally awesome,
I've never shot off
actual fireworks before...
Let's do this thing!
Okay, I'll buy a bucket
and some candles!
Here we go.
Wow...
It's on fire...
It's really on
fire, you guys!
Now, gaze upon my secret fire
magic technique, church lady...!
Burn in the fire of purgatory
and die in obscurity...!
Megiddo flame!
I know that trick, too!
Stop it, no copying me!
So cool...
Rika will take up an interest
in fireworks after this.
Our lives are exactly
like these sparklers...
They shine on,
big and bright...
But the beauty of it
only lasts an instant
before it dies
out completely.
Look, triple sparklers!
Oh grow up;
three is child's play!
Oh, that's beautiful!
Rika is ready for liftoff!
Well, we saved the
best one for last.
This is gonna
be incredible!
That's it?
An utter disappointment
just like our friend Meat there.
And what exactly do
you mean by that?!
Right when I'd given
up on it completely,
it comes through in the end.
Yeah, like me.
That comment wasn't about
you in any way whatsoever.
Look, it's still going...
Rika thinks we're getting
our money's worth.
Hey guys... Is it me,
or does something stink?
You're right...
Rika doesn't think
that's gunpowder either.
Yozora, it's your hair!
It's on fire!
Stop, drop and roll!
Quick, we need water!
-Turn around, Yozora!
-Hurry!
Good job...
You put it out.
Yozora...!
Are you all right?
No.
That poor thing.
For the rest of
summer vacation,
we didn't see Yozora at all.
Not once.
She didn't even
show up to the club.
-Danabe.
-Here.
-Tsuda.
-Hasegawa.
-Yeah.
-Hirasawa.
-Here.
-Fujioka.
-Horiguchi.
-Here.
-Matsushita.
-Yozora.
Mikazuki.
Here.
Well... You made it
in the nick of time...
If I were you
I'd take a seat.
Yes, sir.
Sora?
It's been a while...
Taka.
She's right.
Ten long years...
Feels like forever.
[Music]
So, after the summer
festival fireworks incident,
Yozora didn't show up
at the club like usual.
Ahh! The club room is
so much more relaxing
without that stupid
vixen hanging around!
Chill out, that's not a nice
thing to say, you know?!
Sorry, the
truth's the truth!
This is a problem for me!
I need Yozora here
or I'll go nuts!
Just tell me
what's the matter.
She's how I get
my potato chips!
Oh... Right.
Next time, folks...
We don't have
many friends.
You know, without her here,
it's actually so relaxing,
I'm kinda bored.