Look, guys!
It's Kobato!
Where's Rika?
[MARIA]
Rika is... not here?
Then that means the movie
isn't here, either.
[YOZORA]
Yup.
This is so stupid.
She messaged me late last night
saying it would be done today
no matter what, and we
had nothing to worry about.
So dramatic.
[KODAKA]
Hold on.
Does that mean she
pulled an all-nighter again?
I'm gonna go check on her.
[KODAKA]
Rika!
You in there?
What the-- Why is it unlocked?
Rika?
Rika!
[KODAKA] The doctor said
it was just a cold.
Okay, seriously.
She didn't have
to worry us like that.
[YOZORA]
I was thinking.
Is it possible we put too much
pressure on her by letting her
edit the whole thing by herself?
[KODAKA]
Maybe.
[YOZORA]
Whatever.
We don't have time to waste
worrying about that now.
How is that a waste of time?
[YOZORA]
We can't do anything about it!
We have work to do!
[KODAKA]
What are we gonna work on?
We have to cancel
all the screenings.
Cancel them?
Such a waste of good close-ups.
[YOZORA]
It's not finished.
What else are we supposed to do?
Besides.
It's pointless to have
a premiere of the movie
when all seven
of us aren't there.
I agree.
[AOI]
No touching!
Mitts off the bulletin board!
It's sacred!
Oh, Kodaka.
I didn't recognize you.
Hey, it's okay, Aoi.
Didn't mean to
freak you out like that.
Something came up and my group
had to cancel the presentation
so I was taking
down the posters.
My bad.
Hey, guess what?
Remember that time
I accused you of touching
the bulletin board
and you didn't?
That was dumb.
You're not the kind of
guy who would do that!
I'm sorry, but this is so lame.
I'm not trying to pansy out but
you might be the first person
ever to believe that I'm not
trying to ruin their lives.
[AOI] I'm not trying
to understand anything
you're saying right now, but
it's obvious your heart is
as sweet as the nose on
your perfect little face.
No wonder you and
Sena are together.
You're like an angel-mouse
couple straight out of
a pastry cart!
I could eat you alive!
Put that in park.
Sena's not my girlfriend.
We're in a club together.
[AOI]
Not possible.
I know Sena Kashiwazaki and
home girl's not in any clubs!
She is, but it's
only been since June.
[AOI]
Huh.
"The Neighbors Club"?
I've never heard of this
and I've got at
least four neighbors!
What do you guys do in there?
[KODAKA]
We-- uh.
Right now we just
take these posters down.
[AOI]
Right, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to keep you.
[KODAKA]
All good!
Okay, I guess I'll see ya later!
[AOI]
'Kay!
[KODAKA]
Rika, are you awake?
[RIKA]
Yes.
There's plenty of room
for you in here.
Of course there is.
Ya know, that
joke's getting ol--
[KODAKA]
Wow.
Maybe you shouldn't get better.
Why do you want Rika
to keep suffering from
a terminal illness?
[KODAKA]
No!
I was just joking!
You guys aren't showing
the movie at all anymore?
Nope.
But Rika was so
close to finishing it.
There's no point in making
you do that if you just end up
back in here.
Fine, but it's
seriously almost done!
You guys could show what we have
and nobody would ever know!
Don't be silly.
We're not gonna do that.
[KODAKA] We can't have a
premiere of a movie we all
worked on if not all
of us are there.
That's what Yozora said.
Yozora said that?
[KODAKA]
Yeah.
I was shocked, too, at first,
but I agree with her.
We all do.
So there!
Sorry.
Did that throw off
your game face?
[RIKA, flustered]
Don't be silly!
Everything's fine!
Are you sure?
When she told me,
I almost cried.
[RIKA emotional]
[RIKA fake yawning]
Rika is suddenly very sleepy.
[sheets moving]
[whispering]
Rika has a comment.
Now's a good time for you
to take advantage of Rika.
She's half asleep.
It's fine.
You're insane.
Do you have a backup plan
in case I ever take you up
on one of your smutty offers?
[RIKA]
No.
Rika knows you won't.
Oh!
Rika just had
the best idea ever!
You should read one of her books
to her until she falls asleep!
[KODAKA]
Oh yeah?
[RIKA]
Yeah!
How 'bout this one?
[KODAKA] You want me
to read you boy-love?
Not happening.
[RIKA]
Please?
It's really good!
And Rika's dying!
You're so ridiculous.
It'll make Rika feel better.
You're her only hope.
Oh fine, you pervert, but
I'm gonna talk to your doctor
about this other
sickness you have.
The things I do for you.
This is really
going to help Rika!
Oh good you found the bookmark.
You can start from
the top of the page.
Right.
Uh.
'Kay.
"So he said, 'I know that
you want it bad, whore.
You've been so
desperate for my boy hole.
My ass is hungry, Teacher,
and wants a bite of your--.'
'--a bite of your--'
Speak up!
This is the best part!
Uh.
'--wants a bite of your sweet,
delicious, cocksicle.'
[RIKA]
Commit!
Rika needs to believe you!
[KODAKA]
"He was aroused.
He often caressed himself
to thoughts of that yaoi hole,
and now here he would destroy
it." The heck is a yaoi hole?
Like a secret
compartment on his body?
You're a boy and you don't
know what the yaoi hole is?
Is this real life?
Huh?
[KODAKA]
I asked you first.
[RIKA] Rika can't believe the
yaoi hole doesn't really exist.
And what made you think it did?
[RIKA] How was Rika supposed
to know differently?
She's never actually seen
a boy naked in real life!
And she doesn't have any
friends who want to talk to her
about it, much less show her.
Do you have one and
aren't telling Rika?
Just show her one time!
You need to get some sleep.
I gotta go anyway.
Okay.
[KODAKA] It's cool that we
can joke around like this
and things don't get weird.
I'm really glad
we're friends, Rika.
[PHONE]
"You've got mail!"
[RIKA] "Rika has great
news for you guys!
The movie is finally finished,
so let's meet in the club room."
Ahem.
Rika knows that she
inconvenienced all of you
at the school festival
the other day.
And she wants to apologize.
You mean ruining it?
No problem.
We're all glad
you're feeling better.
I just want to see my face,
so, can we get on with this?
Yeah, c'mon!
I can't wait to
see our big movie!
Show us your fruitless efforts,
if you dare, Tragic Mortal.
Okay, I hope you guys enjoy!
♪
[KODAKA]
I guess that's it.
It's kind of like our own
private Neighbor's
Club school festival.
[MARIA]
Thumbs ready.
Two!
[KOBATO]
Thumbs ready.
Zero!
[MARIA]
Thumbs ready.
Eight!
Use your inside voices!
You're too loud!
[VIDEO GAME]
Oh, no!
He's right behind us!
Help me!
Yes!
Totes beat my high score!
Who is that?
Aoi Yusa!
We're in the same class,
you self-centered hag!
Huh.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You even asked me what time
it was in homeroom once.
Now that you're this close,
your squeaky tone
does sound familiar.
[AOI]
How do you live with yourself?
How does the universe even
allow you to keep living?
So is there something we
can help you with or did you
just want to talk to Sena?
I almost forgot!
[AOI]
You wait right here.
I need to know what
goes on in this club!
All I ever see you do is play!
This is called 'taking a break.'
Put your claws back in.
[AOI] Don't waste your time
trying to cover it up!
I've been keeping tabs on you
jerks for months now, so there!
Really?
What for?
I wanted to see what club
both you and Sena would be in
since it seemed freakish that
you'd be into the same things.
Oh.
Is it really that suspicious?
And?
[YOZORA]
What if we did just play games?
What business is it of yours?
Each club has its own agenda.
The only ones who should have
that info are club members.
Outsiders have
no right to question us.
I'm on the student
council, Lady Pants!
It's my job to
enforce rules here.
And you're in violation!
[KODAKA]
This is awkward.
I'm pretty sure she's
only here to mess with Sena.
They're rivals or something.
That figures.
[YOZORA]
Look, Pinkie.
The Neighbor's Club
is officially recognized
by the school.
Our club rules and practices
have been reviewed and approved.
In compliance with God's law,
we vow to embrace everyone
as neighbors, deepen friendships
on a spiritual level,
and treat everyone with the
kindness that God wants.
"Love thy neighbor as thyself."
In layman's terms,
that means if hanging out
and playing games together
strengthens our bond,
we are following the club rules!
[AOI]
What?
How the hell did
she remember that?
[YOZORA] Sure, we play
video games, we read.
But it's all about spending
quality time with each other
and making friends.
Isn't that what everyone wants?
Isn't that what you want, too?
Someone that you can depend on?
Someone cool you can
always hang out with?
Someone smart
you can learn from?
Someone like me!
It's not about you!
We work very hard to make sure
we're being as friendly and
neighborly as possible to our
members and other students.
Well, I do think having friends
helps students get through
school and makes life more
fun and easier to deal with.
But I think you guys
are doing a crappy job
and should be shut down!
And that sounds like
a personal issue to me.
I mean, is the student
council even allowed to make
club rulings based on
someone's hurt ego?
It's not that.
Look at her!
She is in violation
of school policy!
And so is that one!
School rules
override club rules!
[YOZORA]
What are you talking about?
[AOI]
The dress code!
It's all here in the handbook!
Article five specifically
lists the rules for attire.
Here it is.
"Students are required to
wear their uniform at all times
while on campus as well as
to and from school.
Uniform includes pleated
skirt for girls--"
Yeah, keep reading and you'll
see that section four of article
five lists several exceptions.
One of them is that approved
club meetings don't count
so we can wear street clothes.
Two, three, four.
Oh crap!
You idiot!
That rule only
applies to gym clothes,
which are technically
still part of the uniform!
[YOZORA] Then someone needs
to get the handbook amended
because I know it doesn't say
gym clothes specifically.
Your book of human laws has
no power over me, Mortal.
[KODAKA] Yeah, you're lucky
you're still in middle school.
Who's in middle school?
Violation!
She is not allowed
to be in here!
I am, too!
Check your book.
There's no rule that says
you have to be a certain age
to join a club.
You know very well that
outsiders aren't allowed
on campus, much less
in the building!
Yeah, it does say outsiders
aren't allowed on property
even if accompanied
by a legal student.
[AOI]
Okay, then!
However, middle schoolers are
not considered outsiders!
They may go to school on a
different campus, but they're
still students of Saint
Chronica's Academy, right?
But more importantly,
since when is your own brother
or sister considered
an "outsider?"
And let's talk
about this chapel.
Yeah, it's on campus, it's
open to the public--anyone can
come in here at any time whether
they're thirteen or ninety!
Which means, someone who's a
student and sister of a member
in a public location
can't be an outsider!
[KODAKA]
What she said.
You're okay.
This isn't over!
I'm gonna think of something!
Come here, shoes.
Ugh.
Is there anything we can do to
make sure she doesn't come back?
Conversations with stupid people
make me want to throw up.
Presidential wisdom.
Good work.
Get ready to pack up
'cause I got you this time!
Gross.
Do you still exist?
I really am over your
pointless cockiness.
I happened to find a section
that says this Neighbors Club
crap is definitely in
violation of school rules.
My god, you're obsessed!
Section Two, Rules for
Extracurricular Activities.
Look.
Right here it says,
"as a rule, classes,
clubs and other activities
undertaken in groups,
must be conducted under the
supervision of an instructor!"
That just means we have
to have an advisor present
at all the meetings, doesn't it?
[AOI]
Yeah!
And you don't have
an advisor present!
It says here in
Article seventy-eight.
"Student Council bylaws say that
club advisors must be faculty
or staff of the school!"
Great because in Section Two it
says that a Sister's authority
is equal to that of any
faculty member on campus.
So yeah, we're all good there.
[AOI]
Um, how?
You don't have a Sister
you can call an advisor!
I hope you weren't
referring to Maria Takayama
during that speech, 'cuz
she's not an actual Sister!
That's right.
I checked the roster
of Sisters thoroughly.
There is absolutely
no Maria Takayama listed.
There is someone registered
with that last name
and it's her sister, Kate.
Which means Maria here is
just a random little girl
who hangs out in a chapel.
Illegally!
No freaking way!
We listed her as our club
advisor and it was approved!
Someone on staff made a mistake!
Hold on.
I'm gonna clear this up!
[KATE]
Hey Broseph!
What's up?
[KODAKA]
I need your help with something.
Maria's a Sister, right?
Like, she's legit?
[KATE]
No.
[KODAKA]
Huh?
What do you mean?
[KATE] She's my assistant,
but it's not official.
I'm just trying to help her
develop the skills
for when she gets older.
Plus, it's easier for me
to keep an eye on her
if she's at the same school.
[KODAKA] But why does she tell
everyone she's a teacher?
[KATE]
I don't know!
Great imagination, I guess?
[KODAKA] She wears the nun
outfit every freakin day!
[KATE]
'Cause it's adorable!
Apparently it's true.
She's not a real Sister.
Well, that sucks.
Man, talk about
a bubble being busted.
But if I'm not a real
Sister, then what am I?
[AOI]
That's right, turd-faces!
You don't have an advisor!
And if you don't
have an advisor,
you don't have
a legitimate club!
If you're trying to
form a club illegally,
then you're trying
to get disbanded!
And if that's not
what you're looking for--
[SENA] If Maria were an official
advisor we'd be all good, right?
Yeah, but she isn't one.
Her sister said she was fake.
Uh-huh.
Shut up and wait here a sec.
Uh.
Want coffee?
Huh?
[KODAKA] Don't worry; I promise
no one's trying to poison you.
[YUKIMURA]
Oh no.
Forgive me, sir.
I'm afraid I've
missed the opportunity
to destroy our enemy.
[KODAKA]
Stop.
Hurting her isn't
gonna solve anything.
[SENA] Thank you very much for
your patience, Commoners.
Good news!
Maria's just been offered a
part-time specialty position!
Huh?
[MARIA]
That's nice.
But, what's a part time
specialty person do?
You teach classes part time.
So glad I have the
greatest Daddy in the world.
No way!
Serious?
I'm a real live teacher?
Not just pretend?
[SENA]
Yep.
Think you can handle it?
Totally!
Heck yeah!
[SENA]
Sweet.
We'll add that to
the paperwork, then.
Yay!
I'm a real teacher
in a real school...!
[SENA]
Hey Daddy.
Okay, she accepted.
Yeah.
Okay.
'Kay, bye.
This is ridiculous!
I won't allow it!
Really?
'Cause the president of the
school thinks it's fine.
'Cause you didn't
tell him the whole truth!
Just because you decided to get
an advisor now doesn't mean
the club wasn't
founded illegally!
It's still not legit!
Omigod, shut your flytrap!
Listen and listen well.
No matter how hard you
work to get us shut down,
I can still make a phone
call and have it reversed.
We have an advisor now, okay?
Your narking paid off.
You look like a hero.
You're freaking welcome.
I don't believe you.
You're lying about something.
[SENA] You don't know
when to quit, do you?
This club and
everything in it is mine.
I can do whatever I want;
so if you keep pulling
this student council crap,
you won't be a member anymore!
If you'd rather not deal,
I can have you expelled.
What?
But you can't expel me!
[SENA]
Wanna test it and find out?
You better hope you're right.
Um.
Sorry I ruined your meeting.
I hope you can forgive me.
And the club was saved by the
rich girl who abused her power
and threatened to
have someone expelled.
Well, I guess we know
who the villain is.
Oh whatever!
At least I got it done
and we still have a club!
You made me miss
Kaoru's bunny costume!
Did you do that for the club or
were you just trying to get back
to your stupid bikini game?
Be honest, Sena!
[SENA]
I was trying to finish the game!
At least we know her priorities
will always be the same.
Please.
If that's all it took to get
rid of her, then she's totally
not worth stopping the
game to try to impress.
If she was someone worthy of
respect, she would have ignored
me and kept fighting for what
she thought was actually right.
[KODAKA] I do sort of
feel bad for little Aoi.
But at least we know
if Sena's around,
the Neighbor's Club won't
be shut down any time soon.
[SENA]
Oh.
Kodaka, I have a question!
Actually, Daddy reminded me
of this when we were on
the phone a little while ago.
What?
[SENA]
Just curious.
Would you ever
reconsider marrying me?
It's been on my mind ever since
that whole betrothal thing.
I mean, I've told you before.
I don't care about some
stupid promise our fathers
made to each other ages ago.
That is still true, but
this time it's different.
Now I don't care that
the promise was made,
because even if it's what our
parents want, it's what I want,
too, and I wish I had never
called off the wedding.
I know this
seems kind of random,
but I totes love you and stuff.
It just kinda
makes sense, ya know?
I'm sorry it took me
awhile to realize it.
[KODAKA]
What the hell are you saying?
Hey!
You made me lose
the entire game!
I'm sorry.
So, what were you saying before?
Evs!
I know you heard me!
Whoa.
I, uh, said that
out loud, didn't I?
Well, I was planning to
tell you sooner or later anyway.
Wow.
Yeah.
So um-- Now you know.
Let me know when
you have an answer.
[KODAKA]
Um.
The uh-- that game
you were playing.
It's so loud, I couldn't
hear anything you said.
What was it again?
Are you serious?
Sorry!
There's an important
errand I forgot to run!
Found you, Demon Astaroth!
I have decided today I will
use the magic my teacher
taught me to destroy you!
I admire your spirit, Guernica,
and respect your right to
destroy me, but you should
know-- I am your father!
What?
You're a horse!
How is that even possible?
It's actually a long story.
I don't want to know.
Hang on!
One more, and I'm out!
Join us next time for the final
episode of Haganai Next:
I 'blank' Many Friends!
Shatter the very
soul of my enemy!
Nine Lives Breaker!