[SENA]
I have a question for you.
[KODAKA]
Yeah. What is it?
Why were you talking
to Yozora in that dream?
I mean, if you
went back ten years.
Why was what?
What are you talking about?
She's talking about how
you were sleep talking.
You kept shouting,
"Yozora, Yozora, Yozora!"
Don't you think
that's kinda weird?
[KODAKA]
Are you serious?
Agh, you guys, there's
nothing at all strange about me
showing up in a dream that
took place when he was younger.
We played together when
we were little kids.
You played together?
Like you and Kodaka did?
Did I stutter?
It was a long time ago.
Kodaka moved away from here
for about ten years,
but before that, we both
went to the same school.
We hung out and played
and all that stuff.
So I guess you could
say we were friends.
Friends?
You were?
Well, why have you
never said anything?
Look, we were friends
when we were kids;
it's not like it's personal.
Honestly, I didn't think anybody
would even care about it.
I don't get why
it's such a big deal.
Rika had a feeling
something fishy was up.
You were friends.
Rika didn't expect that, though.
Yeah.
I didn't either.
[IN-GAME GIRL]
Any other suggestions?
[KODAKA]
Guess it's back to normal.
[IN-GAME GIRL]
Okay, then our contribution
to the school festival
is officially...
Thanks.
Hey, that reminds me.
Don't we have
a school festival coming up?
Kodaka.
I believe you just
stepped on a land mine.
Explain that.
No.
Never mind.
In fact, I don't even know
what those words mean.
Whatever, the school festival
is all a lie anyway.
Come on.
You're being ridiculous, and
this time no one's sure why.
[YOZORA]
Think about it.
We're talking about a school
festival here; also known as
an event for people with real
lives also known as not us.
Kay, I see your point.
Uh huh, I thought you might.
Yeah.
I suppose an event
like that has nothing to do
with losers like us, huh?
[SENA]
Shut your mouth!
Don't lump everyone
into Loserville with you.
Just so you know, I'm
a big deal at this school.
And I was all over
last year's festival;
they couldn't get enough of me.
True!
Rika remembers seeing
a lot of Sena last year.
She watched the festivities
from the guest seating,
on the President's
personal invitation.
See, so you can tell them
how amazing I was!
Now go ahead, Rika, and don't
leave anything out, either!
Oh.
Okay, well I saw you in a bunch
of the athletic competitions.
That's right.
Like running the
two hundred meter dash.
As well as the
scavenger hunt race,
and of course
the obstacle course.
I did the bread-eating race.
And I rocked the marathon.
Oh, and my favorite was
the mock cavalry battle!
It was awesome, as was myself.
[KODAKA]
Wow.
That's impressive, Sena.
Thanks; I did the
Culture stuff, too.
I'm more than an athlete.
Right, Rika saw you
in the class play.
Sena bravely cut down all
the bad guys with her sword.
Yeah, no surprise there.
I was the star of the show.
No matter what it was, you
were the one way more into it
than anybody else,
which was awkward.
Everybody there
was super annoyed.
Don't be hateful.
That's not true.
All of the audiences
went crazy over me.
[RIKA]
Well, of course they went crazy.
With your running and jumping,
your boobies jiggled like crazy
all over the place,
so the guys loved it.
They saw your panties
during the play, too.
You're telling me they
weren't mesmerized by my
brilliant performance, they were
excited about a panty shot?
That's so awesome.
Sounds like a tragically
hilarious case of Meat
acting Meat-like to me.
Wow.
You were so close yet oh so far.
[SENA]
I was not.
You shut your face!
See.
This proves the school festival
is no place for
people with no lives.
So we should sit it out
and let them have their fun.
So, Kodaka, I was
wondering, who do you think
you're gonna spend the
day of the festival with?
I know; the Neighbors Club can
present our own special event
in the Culture portion
of the school festival!
No, we can't.
Whaddaya mean we can't?
It's perfect for us.
This kind of cheesy stuff is
pretty much our club's thing.
She's right, if anything's
our formula, it's this.
And, if you think about it,
this will be great practice
for when we go to
festivals with friends.
It can be new research.
Good idea!
No, no it's not!
Rika has no objections to it.
You guys, hold on!
[YUKIMURA] Big Brother's
wish is my command.
Kodaka.
What's wrong now, Yozora?
Nothing, fine!
You're just really stupid.
Very well.
The Neighbors Club
will participate
in this year's school festival.
We shall take hold of those real
lifers in the middle of their
festivities and we'll cast them
into hell where they belong!
Yay hell!
Understood completely.
Yep.
I'm in; let's go!
I dunno.
Casting them into hell
seems a little extreme.
All right, first we have
to decide what we want
to contribute as a group.
[SENA]
How about a maid café?
Go die.
What's wrong with that?
Everyone knows a maid café
is the easiest path
to festival victory.
Don't be such an idiot, Meat.
Isn't it obvious I'm
not the kind of girl who
can wait on customers?
Yeah, I can't imagine Yozora
ever being able to manage that.
Especially not
dressed up as a maid.
I just pictured Yozora
wearing a maid outfit
waiting on customers, and
it was the funniest thing
I've ever imagined.
Oh, my sides!
Sure.
It's true that I'm not
very good at customer service.
So what.
I mean, it's not like
any of you are either!
Hey.
Gimmie a break; I think I can
at least handle that much.
Though I have no experience.
Yeah, right.
If Kodaka tried
customer service all the
customers would run away.
Don't be rude; they would not!
I can act nice
whenever I want to!
But the problem
is you never want to.
Okay, Miss Know-It-All,
then what about you--can
you do customer service?
You should know by now not
to underestimate the power
of genius inventor Rika Shiguma!
Hey, Yozora?
Do you have the maid
costume Yukimura wore when
we thought he was a boy?
Yeah, I think so.
Hold on.
Rika might as well try
the outfit on so she can
practice it right.
Close your eyes.
Rika's going to change
clothes, so no peeking!
Got it.
[RIKA]
You may open your eyes now.
Your face is telling Rika
you've simply acknowledged
Rika is wearing maid clothes.
However, you don't have
any comments in particular
on the matter.
You're right about that.
That was pretty cool;
you just totally read my mind.
You're an imbecile!
Why are you so stupid, Kodaka?
And you kept your eyes closed
the whole time I was changing!
You moron--you were
supposed to sneak a peek!
What for?
[RIKA]
Forget about it.
Listen up, jackwagon.
Get your boneheaded ass
out of this room,
and come back in again!
You know, you've had
a really foul mouth lately.
You twisted twat-face
with pudding for brains!
Ow, jeez, Rika!
What the hell was that for?
Shut up and sit down in your
chair, you fucking clown!
Bitch, I said sit down!
Ow...
You understand you're being
kicked, but for some reason
you can't grasp the idea
of sitting your ass down?
What kind of poorly
trained fleabag are you?
Rika seriously questions
whether there are brains in
that thick skull of
yours, which, by the way,
is the color of her poop
after she eats curry!
Stop!
You can't do whatever
you want just because
you've randomly decided
to be a dominatrix!
Ha!
Rika says ha.
Good grief.
Rika doesn't remember giving
a brainless dog permission
to sit in the chair
of a human being!
Fine.
Then just tell me
where you want me to sit.
There's a chair
right in front of you.
Unfortunately,
it's invisible to fools.
Rika is going to set this
here, but it is not for you.
And, just so you know, the
coffee costs nine hundred
and eighty yen,
is that understood?
I can't believe you're
gonna charge me for coffee
I didn't even order.
And it's expensive.
[RIKA] Whatever, just take off
your pants and pathetically
humiliate yourself in public
by exposing your privates
as you enjoy the diabolical
combination of coffee aroma
and the stench of
your own crotch.
You perverted worm.
[KODAKA]
Please.
I'm begging you.
I can't take any more.
Oh.
Promise that you'll
come back to see Rika again!
[KODAKA]
Not on your life!
Come on, admit it.
You love seeing Rika like this!
How can I admit to
liking something that
was so brutal to me?
Well, that's unexpected.
Rika was sure this attitude
would be quite popular.
Illogical thought process aside,
this could be a good
direction for us to take.
Nope.
I beg to differ on that.
What did you think, Yukimura?
[YUKIMURA] I'm afraid
your skills are still
somewhat immature.
Oh.
Well, you're a former maid,
right, so, do you think
you could teach us the essence
of what a real maid should be?
[YUKIMURA]
Yes.
The essence of a maid.
Simple.
It is complete and utter
devotion to Big Brother.
Okay, you're up next.
Care to give us a little taste
of your customer
service skill set?
Uh.
You wanna see me?
[RIKA]
Rika knows she does!
Come on, Sena.
Rika bets you're
really good at it.
[SENA]
Guess I don't have a choice.
All righty, Kodaka.
I'm gonna change now,
so go wait in the hallway.
I can't just close my eyes
like I did before?
[SENA]
No, of course not!
I mean, we already have two
full strikes on our record, so.
Our what?
[SENA]
Never mind!
Just get out of here!
What's her problem?
[SENA]
You can come in now, Kodaka!
Welcome home, Master.
How has your day been?
[KODAKA]
Uh.
Is that too small?
Stop staring at me
like that, gah.
How did you two fit into this;
it's like crazy tight;
I can barely even breathe.
Holy shit.
You can say that again.
Okay, holy shit.
[SENA]
What would you like?
We have special maid sandwiches.
Special maid tea and coffee.
Special maid yummy cake.
We have what ever
your little heart desires,
so what'll it be, Master?
Coffee I guess.
That sounds great.
[SENA]
Coffee it is.
Coming right up, Master!
I'm really confused right now.
How come you're
so good at doing this?
It's not all that confusing.
Uh.
I'm just uh-- Oh!
I'm just copying
Stella, that's all!
Is that what it is?
You have a
professional butler at home,
so that's almost the same thing?
Totally.
Almost exactly.
So you have a
professional butler.
I fail to see how watching
a butler would make you
the perfect café maid.
Well, whatever it is,
you're really good.
Stop flattering me, silly.
Wait, I forgot.
I have to do a spell
to make it taste better!
What kind of spell?
Taste better,
taste better, now.
Oh!
Kay!
Yummy!
Um.
That kind.
Really?
Uh.
Yes, Miss Master.
Really, really, really.
Really?
Yep.
Haha.
Really.
Really, Meat?
No, I don't visit maid cafes
as much as I can when I'm not
in school, leave me alone!
All right.
Maid cafes are off the table.
See ya; I'm heading home now.
Cool.
Oh, right.
Hey, Yozora, I forgot I had
something to ask you.
[YOZORA]
No, wait.
It's not.
I uh.
This isn't what
it looks like, Kodaka.
I swear to you!
Uh.
I have reasons.
I mean.
Wait.
No!
Leos!
[FEMALE TV HOST] This week,
be sure and keep your eyes out
for a disturbance in the force.
Because, if you don't have
the right attitude about it,
you might end up
hurting your friends.
All my Virgos will need...
Like I have any friends anyway.
What are you doing today?
Do you have any more
make up classes?
I do not, today marks the end
of my two week long ordeal.
I am free to live as I please.
Must be a relief, huh?
Maybe next time try not
to fail your classes.
[KODAKA]
Hm, let's see.
I like the idea of
a fortune telling booth.
Please tell me you don't
really believe in that stuff.
[KODAKA]
Well.
Not personally, no.
But I guess I thought a lot
of people liked having
their fortunes told.
'Specially high school girls.
Not me; I don't
buy any of that BS.
I mean, when
you're chosen by God,
every day is your lucky day.
I don't need some wrinkled,
old hag to tell me
how wonderful my life is.
[YOZORA]
You're exactly right, Meat.
You are blessed and
every day is your lucky day.
[SENA]
Yozora.
So you admit the truth?
I do.
You've been lucky every
single day of your life.
Meaning you've
hit your luck ceiling.
There's nowhere else to go.
You will never
make a new friend.
The girls at school will
forever hate and shun you,
so they'll keep ganging
up on you, which means
you'll always be
alone in gym class.
When people pair up
for home ec or a field trip,
someone will inevitably say,
"Hey, Sena, why don't you
pair up with a boy?" And
then everyone will laugh.
Your memories will be ruined.
And right now is the happiest
your life will ever be.
[SENA]
Rude much?
How can you say that?
For what it's worth.
Rika thinks you should just
try to be happy anyway.
I feel so sad, now.
Poor, poor Sena.
You don't really
believe her, do you?
[YOZORA]
Still though.
I think I can get behind
the fortune telling idea.
[KODAKA] Are you a believer
in that kind of thing, Yozora?
No, I absolutely am not.
For three months in middle
school, I checked every fortune
I could get my hands on.
TV, newspapers, magazines,
I checked them all.
I also recorded in detail
everything that happened to me
on those days.
Afterwards.
I objectively assessed
my so-called "luck",
tallied it against
all the fortunes,
and collected the statistics.
Not a single fortune had
an accuracy rate higher
than seven percent.
Therefore!
I decided I could not
believe in fortune telling.
By taking it to that extreme
you seem more than
a little fortune obsessed.
For real.
More importantly,
why are you agreeing to do
the booth after all that?
[YOZORA] All we have to do is
make up a bunch of random crap.
Then we'll be able to screw
over all the real-life-havers
who are unintelligent enough to
take fortune telling seriously.
I can't imagine anything
more fun than that.
[KODAKA]
How cruel.
[SENA] You're an actual
witch, aren't you?
[YUKIMURA] If you ask me,
I think you sound crazy.
[YOZORA]
Meat.
I'll read your fortune
as an experiment.
Why would you wanna do that?
Yes.
I see it.
[SENA]
Uh.
See what?
[YOZORA] Something is troubling
thee right now, is it not?
[SENA]
Troubling me?
For real?
Thee?
[YOZORA] Tis something to
do with thy relationships.
Well.
Now that you mention it, yeah.
I guess that's accurate.
[YOZORA]
I know.
Thou art giving off
a faint purple mist,
a mist that
symbolizeth uneasiness.
I can tell from the shape
of the mist that relationships
are the root of this trouble
in your life right now.
Wow.
You're right.
A hundred percent.
Yes, because I see-eth
and knoweth all things.
I can also tell, thou
generally thinkest in a manner
which brings about
a positive attitude.
However, occasionally
thou feelest regret.
How could you know all that?
And here we go.
Thou hast certain gifts.
Gifts that are far and above
what those you find around you
have been given.
Yet I can sense thou are often
frustrated at not being able
to express these gifts
to their fullest.
Though thou hast an optimistic
side, at times thou waverest
about thy actions and
decisions, growing worrisome.
And whilst thou art
normally cheerful.
Thou art also prone
to great loneliness.
Impossible!
Tell me how you know that!
[KODAKA]
Hey.
This type of reaction
has a name, doesn't it?
Yeah; that's right;
it's called the Barnum effect.
It's a psychological
phenomenon wherein the subject,
when told general things
that could apply to anyone,
takes them to be an accurate
personal diagnosis.
You know, I honestly didn't
expect you to understand me
so well, Yozora.
How funny.
It's making me
feel happier in a way.
And, she fell for it hook,
line, and sinker.
Shocking.
I am willing to tell thee a way
to immediately improve the life
of a sweet yet awkward
person such as thyself
if thou art willing to listen.
Really?
Tell me, I'm listening!
[YOZORA] Tonight at midnight
on the dot, thou must go
to the roof and balance a
bowl of water upon thy head,
turning around three times
whilst giving an eerie shriek
and shouting, "Sexy Beam!"
loud enough for the
whole house to hear.
If the water doth not spill
from the bowl, thou shalt attain
the moon's blessing,
and thy life will be visited
by great fortune.
Shut the hell up.
Oh, thank you, Yozora.
I've misjudged you,
and I'm so sorry.
It's not a problem.
Go forth now.
May thee... be happy.
[PHONE]
You've got mail.
Sena?
[SENA]
Daddy spanked me so hard,
but I don't mind if
it's for my happiness!
Sexy beam!
Oh, crap; don't tell me
she actually did it.
Yozora!
What do you want, Meat?
Don't you--
Don't you "what do you want" me.
You skank.
How dare you
trick me like that?
Trick you?
Why whatever do you mean?
That fortune telling yesterday.
You made up
that stupid mean lie.
It was so mean.
And hateful.
And then--
Hey, don't let
your dad get you so upset.
His favorite pastime is yelling
at you about the stupid stuff
you always do;
it's kinda his thing.
That's not the issue!
Yesterday, I felt so happy.
I had hope again.
You-- I don't know,
you just really--You just--
you're so mean.
And dumb.
You're mean and dumb.
I feel like crap,
so I hope you're happy.
Come on.
Let's go ahead and go
to the clubroom, okay?
I have been awaiting
your arrival, my other half.
Oh, hi--
Yay!
You're here!
It feels like it's
been forever, right?
What up, girl?
Did you just come by
to hang out with me?
Too cute!
Oh, you are my angel!
It's true, your
angelicness is...
Kodaka, help!
[KOBATO]
Shut up.
I don't like this.
Why do you always talk
like a crazy person?
What the hell
are you looking at?
Oh, nothing, never mind.
How lucky am I that I get to
see you today, am I right?
[YOZORA]
It seems that good fortune
has visited you after all.
You're right.
I think I'm like totally
back on a roll again!
What on Earth could be luckier
than being visited by Kobato?
Look.
She's just here 'cause
she doesn't have to stay
after school to make up
classes any more.
Yes.
I suppose that is right.
This has nothing what so ever
to do with Yozora's mean old
fake magic.
So you say, but how will
you ever know for sure?
Y'know, that right there
is why nobody likes you.
Well.
It's whatever.
I'll forgive you this time.
There's no sense being mad
when Kobato's here.
Like I care what spoiled
meat thinks about me.
Glad you're
finally back with us.
[RIKA] So have we decided
whether or not we're doing
the fortune telling booth
for the festival, yet?
Rika brought reference books
with her just in case.
Cool.
I dunno, Rika.
I guess we can decide later.
Agreed.
Birthday Fortune-Telling?
Oh.
Hey, that reminds me,
guys, Kobato's got
a birthday next week.
Wait, seriously,
Kobato's birthday?
That's what I said.
It's October
eighteenth, every year.
We have to celebrate, obviously.
You heard me.
We're having a
birthday party for Kobato!
At last, I have returned
victorious from my long
and brutal battle to the death!
Yeah, congratulations.
Now, study every day so you
don't fall behind and have to
make the next test up.
I only failed that last exam
because the akashic records
randomly malfunctioned on me.
No more excuses, young lady.
Get to studying!
Yeah, okay.
Next time: He's My Brother,
But As Long As There's Love,
It Doesn't Matter If He
Gets More Sisters, Right?
Wait!
Yes it does matter!