[doorbell ringing]
Can you get that?
I'm afraid the dinner
will burn if I step away.
If it's someone trying
to sell us newspapers again,
just tell them we can't read.
You're not moving.
[KOBATO sighing, footsteps]
[KOBATO]
No one's home!
I guess that means
it was a salesman.
[KOBATO]
Go away!
We don't have room for all that!
Did your ears fall off?
I said go away!
[KODAKA]
What's going on?
[KOBATO]
Get out of here!
Ain't nobody got time for you!
It's my Big Brother!
Maria?
I'm so glad I found you!
I missed you so much!
Ew, gross!
What are you doing in our house?
I told you we
didn't want you here!
What's with the random visit?
You okay?
I'm a fun-time-lay!
Huh?
No, wait!
Wrong phrase!
I meant to say I'm a runaway!
Yeah, you may want
to be careful with that.
Wait, you ran away?
Uh-huh!
That bossy ol' hag was always
telling me how to do my job!
I told her, "My Big Brother
would never talk to me
like that!' So she said,
"That's fine.
Why don't you go and live
with your Big Brother then?"
So, you actually left
and came over here?
Yep!
[phone ringing]
[KODAKA]
Hello?
[GRUNGY VOICE]
Hey man, it's me.
What it do?
That's the worst impression
of a guy I've ever heard.
But nice try, Kate.
[KATE]
Good job!
Look how smart you are!
I should've known you'd guess!
[KODAKA]
Right.
Well, I'm glad you called.
Maria just showed up here
randomly and I don't know wh--
[KATE]
I know.
Could you keep her
for a couple days?
I'd really appreciate it.
[KODAKA]
What?
Um, I can bring her back
if you want?
[KATE]
Is she bothering you?
[KODAKA]
Well, no but--
What?
What are you looking at,
poopy vampire?
[KOBATO]
Shut-it, Dummy!
[KATE]
You're the best!
Love you, mean it!
No problem.
Oh wow.
I've never seen
so much food in my life!
It looks just like Christmas!
Yeah?
Well, not quite.
Is it someone's birthday?
What's happening?
God sure has some
annoying minions.
You're exactly what's
wrong with the human race.
Let's eat!
[MARIA]
Stop!
What the heck is wrong with you?
I don't remember
seeing you pray for that!
Heathen!
I belong to the Night Tribe.
I do not know this God
of whom you speak.
[KODAKA]
Kobato!
You don't have to give a sermon,
but you can at least say
"thanks for the food."
Thanks for the food, I guess.
[KODAKA]
Nice.
I'm proud of you.
[MARIA]
Hey!
You can't just start without us!
O Heavenly Father,
thank you for this food
we are about to receive.
May it nourish our bodies
and keep us strong--
Ah, sweet crap!
Amen!
It's so yummy!
Um, I don't remember you
finishing your prayer,
hypocrite!
God will understand that
I'm saving this chicken from
the mouth of an evil vampire!
Whatever!
That's cheating!
It's the truth!
[KOBATO]
No, it's not!
You made that up!
Don't argue with food
in your mouths, guys.
You're gonna choke.
[phone ringing]
Yeah, hello?
[heavy breathing]
[perverted voice]
Hey there, sexy.
What color underwear
are you wearing?
What do you want now, Kate?
[KATE]
Wow, you're good at this.
Anyway, no big deal.
Just wanted to see
if you're eating dinner.
[KODAKA] Yep. They're
at the table right now.
[KATE]
Okay, good.
Promise me you'll make sure
Maria eats all her vegetables
before dessert?
Uh-huh.
[KODAKA]
Great.
Which one of you ate my dinner?
[BOTH]
She did!
By the way, Maria, I'm really
impressed that you actually
found our house on your own.
I never would have
been able to find it!
The hag dropped me off here!
That's not exactly
running away, then, is it?
[phone ringing]
[KODAKA]
Hello?
Hey!
So, how'd it go?
Did Maria eat all her veggies?
She ate a lot more than that.
[KATE]
Good to know!
Love you, mean it!
[KOBATO]
Big Brother?
Good news.
I'll allow you
to play a game with me.
Look at that!
It's a porno game!
[KOBATO]
No, it is not!
Yeah, I don't believe you.
She's telling you the truth.
It's a pretty normal game.
Do you want to try it out?
Oh heck yeah!
[VIDEO GAME]
Ready.
Fight!
K.O!
You win!
Perfect!
[GUERNICA]
That was easy.
You silly human.
How foolish you were to
think you could ever be
a match for me!
Not pulling any
punches, are you?
And now, Darkness Requiem!
[MARIA]
Come on.
Please, you gotta wake up!
[VIDEO GAME]
K.O!
You win!
[GUERNICA]
We fall into eternal darkness.
I win again.
How predictable.
I was so close!
Why did you throw magic
on me at the last minute?
[KODAKA]
Let's go guys.
Time for you both
to take a bath.
A bath?
You mean all by myself
at Big Brother's house?
Yay!
I'm going first!
Hold those please!
Thank you!
What the--
Hey!
The bathroom is over this way!
[MARIA]
Oh!
Woops!
Me and Big Brother
take the same bath!
[phone ringing]
[KODAKA]
Maria's taking a bath, Kate.
[KATE] Make sure she
scrubs behind her ears.
She always forgets.
Are you actually
that worried about her?
[KATE]
No!
I'm never worried
about anything ever!
Pretty!
It looks just like
fluffy white doody!
[KODAKA]
Hey Maria?
I'm leaving you
some PJs by the door.
They're Kobato's
so they should fit.
Don't stay in there too long.
I made white doody!
Ha!
Watch this!
Bam! Yeah.
[MARIA]
Uh, Big Brother?
What's wrong, Maria?
It doesn't fit.
Do you have
anything else I can wear?
[MARIA]
It's too tight.
Especially up here.
I don't think I'll
be able to sleep in it.
[KODAKA]
Okay, sorry about that.
I guess that means you'll have
to find somewhere else to go!
[KODAKA]
Kobato, calm down.
What's gotten into you?
It's Big Brother's t-shirt!
Oh my gosh, it's like
we're connected!
You are quite a
foolish Godly minion.
Once this battle is over you
will regret your mockery!
Please.
Your threats don't scare me,
you smelly vampire
I wouldn't do that
if I were you!
[VIDEO GAME]
K.O!
You win.
[GUERNICA]
That was easy.
That will teach you not
to question my powers.
You're already exhausted?
Not worth it.
They say children
grow best in their sleep.
I'm going to sleep, too!
What was that about?
All right.
Time for me to pass out, too.
[phone ringing]
Aw man.
[KATE]
Is Maria in bed yet?
It's late.
[KODAKA]
She is.
[KATE]
Good.
Hey.
Are you obsessed
with your sister?
Tell the truth.
[KATE]
I am not obsessed with anyone!
Screw yo--!
[phone ringing]
What now?
[KATE] Yeah, I need to know
if she brushed her teeth be--
I will never sleep again
as long as Maria's here.
This has to end.
Just hang in there.
We're almost done, okay?
[KATE]
Not so fast, Kiddo.
Apologize to Big Brother for
all the trouble you caused him.
[MARIA]
Um.
I'm very sorry for
causing you trouble.
[KODAKA] She's not the one
who should be apologizing.
[KATE]
I owe you for this!
[KODAKA]
No big.
I'm glad I could help.
[MARIA] So does that mean I
can stay over again sometime?
Of course.
You're always welcome here.
No, she's not!
Don't ever come back!
I didn't ask you,
you disgusting vampire!
I'll come back whenever I want!
Big Brother said so!
Bye bye!
[KODAKA]
Glad that's over.
One day more and they
would've killed each other.
Only stupid little babies
run away from home.
[KODAKA] Man, I guess
that really got to her.
Die, fiend!
Hey, isn't it too early
to be playing video games?
I must build up my
magic skills to prepare for
the random invasions of
God's foolish minions.
Next time she's here, she will
have no choice but to submit
to my overwhelming powers!
[KODAKA]
"Next time she's here," huh?
Seriously?
School's only been out for
three days and already there's
nothing left for us to do.
You make an interesting point.
Do you have any idea what all
the normal students are doing
to kill time these days?
And how would I know that?
Rika has seen many manga
where people are having
hilarious parties
together after finals.
Rika thinks they were called
"Forget Your Cares" parties.
[KODAKA]
Oh yeah, I've heard of those.
I see.
Yeah, okay, maybe we
should give that a try.
What goes into planning
something like that?
[SENA] I didn't go through the
stress of studying for exams,
so I don't have
any cares to forget.
Then I guess you're not
participating with us?
I'm so exhausted from thinking
about worrying about finals!
[YOZORA]
I understand.
If you're that tired,
maybe you need to go take
a nap in the nurse's office.
[SENA]
What do you mean?
Come to think of it.
Rika didn't take the exams
either so she's not stressed.
Um.
Teachers don't have
to take the exams,
but can I still
come to the party?
Of course; if that's
what you want to do!
Fine, I guess I'll go, too.
Sorry.
Can't.
There's only room for about six
people at these kind of parties.
Shut up!
You're just saying
that to be mean!
Why do you hate me?
[YOZORA]
All right.
Does everyone
have a drink ready?
--[GROUP] Yep!
--[RIKA] Rika does!
Okay.
Then drink up.
Wait! Hold on a sec!
Aren't you supposed to make
a toast or something?
Oh.
Okay.
This is a toast
to finals being over.
So, cheers and stuff.
[GROUP]
Cheers and stuff!
[MARIA]
Where are the snacks?
You gonna be okay?
I'm fine.
This is embarrassing, but
my body seems to have a bit
of trouble with
carbonated beverages.
Then why the heck
would you pour yourself one?
I noticed it's what you're
drinking so I wanted to try it.
If I want to be as wonderful a
man as you I can't let a little
carbonation get in my way.
[KODAKA]
Whoa!
Holy crap, are you
sure you're good?
I'm fine.
Thanks.
Forgive me for being such
a useless servant to you.
Here, why don't I go ahead
and drink the rest of this?
Maybe grab some orange juice
or milk instead?
Um.
Hey, Big Brother?
OMG!
Indirect kiss!
[KODAKA]
When did you turn nine?
Please.
[YOUNG KODAKA]
Hey, are you all right?
Orange juice?
So is carbonation still
hard for you to handle?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Of course I can handle it!
I just don't want to, okay?
'Still?' Like since when?
[KODAKA]
Um. Nothing.
Don't worry about it.
[KODAKA] Crap, I forgot my past
with Yozora is supposed to be
a secret.
Something funny's going on here.
[YOZORA]
There.
We already drank and ate snacks
so what's next on the agenda?
Do you guys wanna play a game?
Party games are always fun.
Rika thinks we should
play the King Game.
I've never heard of that.
How do you play that one?
We all draw sticks
to pick who's the king.
If it ends up being you,
then you get to make another
player do anything you want.
It's hilarious.
Anything, really?
Like if I wanted Yozora
to lick the dirt off my feet,
I could do that?
Yeah, the King's orders are
supposed to be absolute,
so if you wanted to take it
in that direction you could.
Oh yeah! I'm in!
Let's play this game of thrones!
That's fine.
Someone needs to put that
Dingbat in her place and
I'm glad we'll be able
to make a game out of it.
Okay, hold on.
We can only play this game
under one condition.
[KODAKA] We're all going to draw
the orders out of this box.
So instead of one person doing
it, we all write down orders
and place them in here.
[SENA] Yeah, I don't
think I like that rule.
[KODAKA] Maybe if everyone faces
the same risk the orders
won't be too brutal.
Okay.
Does everyone have a stick?
One, two.
[GROUP] Three! Show us
the king's orders!
Heck yeah!
I'm so the King!
Obvi, I'm the only one suited
for that title anyway.
Stop trying to form words
and draw an order, please.
Ya know, you might want
to watch your mouth.
Talking to a king that way could
get you in loads of trouble.
And the order is.
Number Four puts on a swimsuit!
What?
Four puts on a swimsuit?
Who wrote that order?
[SENA]
That would be me!
Why'd you do that?
What if that command
was drawn for you?
Would you want to
put on a swimsuit?
The thing is, I would never
draw my own order, silly.
So don't you worry.
Well, which one of you
lucky ducks is it?
Who gets to hang around
in a teeny tiny swimsuit
with practically your entire bod
showing while the rest of us
sit back fully
clothed judging you?
P.S.
no one-pieces are allowed.
It's me.
No!
It can't be Kobato!
I declare this order invalid!
It never happened!
My deepest sympathies, but
once a king's order is given,
it is deemed absolute.
I know your innocence
is threatened.
If you need someone to blame,
take it out on
this tyrant over here.
[SENA]
It's not my fault!
But it's totally okay.
We don't have any swimsuits!
You can't swim in it,
but I think mine'll work!
Oh my gosh.
I'm so sorry Kobato.
I don't forgive you.
You are evil and
you must be destroyed.
I'm sorry!
I didn't think you
would be the one to draw it!
[GROUP]
Go!
Who's the king?
Oh.
Looks like it's me.
Ugh.
Seriously, you people
disgust me to death.
Hey, who's Number Five?
'Cause some jerk decided you
get to read this out loud.
Yes!
That's me!
I win!
I'm Number Five!
Let's see here.
"Oh.
That's so good.
Yeah.
I'm close.
I'm so close.
Oh yeah.
Right there.
Give it to me harder.
Yeah, harder.
Oh yeah!"
You're sick.
Why would you want someone
to read that out loud?
How did you know it was Rika?
She obviously didn't get
what she was reading
so put that snarl away.
Rika hoped to see someone
who understood turn red
and squirm with embarrassment.
Gross.
Moving on.
[SENA]
Looks like I'm the king again!
And the next order will be--
[FEMALE CLERK]
Good afternoon!
[SENA] Tell me, was someone
with my face just in here?
[FEMALE CLERK]
Excuse me?
[SENA]
That wasn't me.
It was Lupin, you rube!
[FEMALE CLERK]
Thank you and have a good day!
Which one of you monkey turds
put that wad of crap on paper?
It doesn't even make sense!
Why would the king
give herself an order?
That's the game, Miss Lobotomy.
All the king's orders
are final and absolute.
Even the orders
she makes for herself.
[KODAKA] I guess we know who
wrote that one down.
No way!
She dog-eared the corner so
she'd know not to draw it.
Classic.
Forever the closet coward.
So.
Number One has to take off their
shirt and show their chest.
Wow, that one's really low.
You go, Kodaka!
Way to stick it to 'em hardcore!
Slow down!
I didn't write that one!
[SENA]
No, he didn't!
That would be yours truly.
[KODAKA]
You've got to be kidding.
And what if you had
drawn that number?
Were you prepared to strip down?
And what makes you think
that would ever happen to me?
I don't understand
where this delusional
confidence comes from.
[RIKA] Alright, so who's
showing us their jugs?
Because it's
definitely not Rika.
[MARIA]
Mine are bigger than yours!
Okay, this next round
is the last one.
[GROUP]
Which one of us is the king?
Oh!
It looks like it's me again!
What.
[SENA]
Come on little blue box!
Make Yozora lick my feet!
Hey, what is that?
It looks like there's
one stuck to the bottom.
Okay, here we go.
This better be worthy
of being the last order.
Are you ready?
It says.
'Number Three has to kiss
the king on the lips.'
[RIKA] Rika was wondering if we
were ever gonna get down
to the sticky stuff!
Fine.
Which one is Number Three?
I am.
[KODAKA] Wow! You're
gonna kiss each other?
You're just like grown ups!
Oh.
Awkward.
You guys all blow.
Let's get this
over with, Kodaka.
What?
We're seriously going to do it?
[SENA]
We don't have a choice!
King's orders are
absolute, remember?
I didn't make the rules!
Oh, yeah.
The rules. Right.
[heart beating]
Intermission!
Um.
Inner what?
[YOZORA]
Not okay!
Why would you degrade yourselves
in front of your peers?
Aren't you the one who said
'kings orders are absolute?'
Shut up!
Both of you are above
this stupid crap!
[SENA]
Are you possessed right now?
[KODAKA]
I've got it!
There.
Mission accomplished.
See?
This is Sena's glass.
So, we just had
an indirect kiss.
On the lips and everything.
I mean, that is still
a thing, isn't it?
Are we in the clear?
Nope!
Just kidding.
Rika approves.
Yeah, I'll allow it, too!
It's okay with me.
Me too!
So that means the king
game is officially over!
Now, let's go
clean this mess up!
Well, it wouldn't have been
as good as just part of a game.
[phone ringing]
[KODAKA]
Hello?
[HAYATO]
Hey Sport!
Long time no chat!
Oh hey Dad.
This is a surprise.
[HAYATO]
Everything going all right?
How are you and Kobato doing?
Fine.
We're both doing fine.
So, what's up?
Do you need something or--?
[HAYATO] Well, I'm hoping
it's not a huge deal but
Zaki told me something
the other day.
Who's Zaki?
Oh.
You mean Sena's dad?
[HAYATO]
That's right.
Be honest, son.
Are you marrying
his little girl?
[KODAKA]
What?
That was kind of a messed
up Forget Your Cares Party,
wasn't it?
It was supposed to be
about relieving stress!
But it just made me
even more stressed out.
The way you put that
was incredibly poetic!
I learn so much
from your words of wisdom!
You totally missed the point!
Oh, you need to stop
being so modest!
This has nothing
to do with modesty!
Join us again next time for,
"A Man Is Among Them!"
That must be talking about me.
Oh, that's right.
I always forget you're a dude.