Oh, hey.
Sena.
Damn meat.
She has some nerve
ignoring me like that.
I'm pretty sure I'm the
one she was ignoring.
Oh, yes!
Conquer me, oh
naughty knight!
I want more in my hand
than just my scepter;
Hey, just what the hell do you
think you're doing, Yozora?
Get your claws off!
What is this?
You heard what I said!
Hands off, you harpy!
Subjugate me!
Grant me your legendary
rigid blade, I beg you!
Ohhh! Good sir, you are truly
a "knight" to remember!
[Music]
Geez! What the hell
are you doing?
I should be the one
asking you that, Jugsy!
What kind of pervert
watches smut in a church?
It is not smut, you idiot!
It's "Blackstar,
the Sacred Sword,"
and it's one of the
hottest video games
on the market right now!
An epic, romantic fantasy
adventure for the ages!
It's loaded with
action and romance.
The brave knight Lucas
has to defeat Varnibal,
the god of destruction.
In the scene you so
rudely interrupted.
Princess Cecilia was proclaiming
her true love for Lucas.
She was opening her
castle gates to him!
Didn't you know it was one
of those adults only games?
No, how was I supposed to?
After "Sparkling
School Life Seven,"
I wanted a new game so I checked
out some online forums.
They all said this was
the hottest game right now.
And then when I asked
this guy in class about it
he gave me a copy and said
it would be perfect for me.
It sure was, pervert!
Are you jealous or
just drinking haterade?
As if, you freak!
Perv--bag!
Sicko! Kink--meister!
Porn addict!
Double--D deviant!
Pneumatic--knockered
nympho!
Get away before I catch
porn--itis from you!
Why do I have to put up
with abuse like this
just for playing a videogame?
Okay, fine,
I'll admit the game
does have a couple
of steamy scenes in it.
But that isn't anything
out of the ordinary.
Go to the library
once in a while
and you'll see
the same thing
you're giving me crap
for in the classics,
so slow your roll!
This game's a work of art,
just like they are!
I've never seen your
eyes glued to art
the way they were
to that game.
Just be honest and admit
you're addicted
to the pervy stuff!
No, I'm not!
I just wanted to help
Lucas and Cecilia
consummate their
relationship!
To help them
do what happens
when a man and woman fall
in love with each other!
What you're seeing
here is love not sex!
Put your nasty porn away!
There's nothing nasty
about it at all!
You could have fooled me.
I'm sorry that you're
such a freaking prude
you can't appreciate the
artistic merits of this scene!
Well if it is art.
Then please read what they're
saying out loud Jiggles.
Uh.
If it truly is an
inoffensive work of art
then you should have no
problem doing what I asked.
Right?
Of course not!
It's just that.
I get a little nervous reading
out loud in front of people.
In that case,
I'll do it, too.
-Huh?
-Say what?
I'll also read
from an artistic work,
but Boobs has to go first.
It's just art right?
She shouldn't have a problem
if that game isn't smut
and the heroine isn't
some promiscuous princess,
hoping to get ahold
of Lucas' "mighty sword"
or his fabled
family jewels.
Hey, don't turn
their pure love
into something that's dirty!
Okay! If you want me
to read it out loud,
then I'll do it!
"Um, my dear Lucas.
Please cleave
my, um, heaving
bosom with your rigid blade.
"Louder I can't hear you!
"And. Let me hold the sword
that makes maidens coo.
I want to see it and
the masterful strokes
that you so deftly
employ in its use.
Show me your big weapon.
"Oh, so you want
me to unsheathe
my sacred sword, do you?
My, what a randy
and demanding tart
you've revealed
yourself to be, Cecilia.
"No. You speak coarse
things that are not true.
"Nonsense, I can see
that lusting expression
in your eyes.
"Look, if you
want something.
Don't deny it;
ask for it.
Or to be more specific,
beg for it, tart!"
"Please, I beg of thee,
my carnal cavalier!
This randy--minded
royal wants- nay, needs.
Your sacred sword!"
"Don't say 'sacred sword.
Say the name of
what you really want.
"Don't stop now.
Go on and finish it off.
"Lucas, please.
I want it, all of it.
Your throbbing, gigantic,
mighty, ravishing-"
I can't say that!
You suck, Yozora!
You're the worst!
That was a bit overboard,
even for you.
I hope the audio
came out okay.
I was recording Meat the
whole time she was reading.
I think I'll play her
little smut recital
over the PA system.
Are you the devil?
Now my turn.
For what?
I said I would do it
and I'm keeping my word.
So I'm going to read from a
work of art like I promised.
"Why does my heart
feel so ashamed.
Autumn mountain shadow
on a day of white wind.
Uncannily mature
tree trunks stood.
In hollows thick with
the fallen leaves.
Wow, that's pretty deep.
Feel my dark wrath
light--bearer!
Hey, Sis, I'm home.
Ah, my mortal servant
has finally returned!
Your vampiric master
is quite famished,
so I do hope you've
brought me a sacrifice.
I'll get dinner
started, Kobato.
That name is only
my human alias.
My proper name is Rasis
Vi Felicity Sumeragi.
Child of Darkness and True
Heir to the great Night Tribe.
I must quench my
thirst and feed, worm!
Bring forth my
sustenance now,
or grave disaster
will befall you!
Whatever, nightspawn.
You'll never
defeat the light!
-Dinner's ready, Sis.
-Oh, yeah?
Your "sacrifice".
Well done, slave.
A human's lifeblood is
incredibly delicious.
It's tomato juice, dork.
And now, here's a tale
of two furry felons.
Remember Chim--Chim,
the young monkey at
the Takayama Zoo who,
Hey, eat your onions,
too, Kobato!
Here.
Attagirl.
By the way,
my human brother.
I've noticed that
you've been late
providing my
sacrifices recently.
Oh, right, I haven't been
getting home as early as usual
because of the club.
You better get used to it.
What's more important to you;
me or that club of yours?
The club, of course.
If you want dinner early,
make it yourself.
We're out of tomato juice.
I mean we're out of the
precious lifeblood of humans.
I'll get some tomorrow.
Thanks, Kodaka.
I mean, you better get it.
You human wretch.
This should brighten
your day, thy dark fiend!
About a year ago,
my kid sister Kobato
got addicted to
this anime series
called "Full Metal Necromancer."
Since then, she's been
acting and talking like
she's this character on
the show who's a vampire.
I spent my first couple
of years in this house
when I was a little kid.
We left it ten years ago
when my Dad had to move
because of work and it's
been sitting empty ever since.
When Dad found out
he was getting transferred
to America recently.
He decided Kobato and
I would stay in Japan.
So "her vampiric majesty"
and I moved back here.
But it's been so long,
I barely remember anything
about this place at all.
Kobato, your bath's ready!
After this show, mortal!
I guess the club really
is important to me.
Hey. Why aren't you
playing "Porn Star" today?
That's "Black Star,"
you idiot!
I didn't want
any more crap
so I brought "Sparkling
School Life Seven,"
but it appears the
harpy isn't here.
She said some book she
wants goes on sale today.
Hey, tell me something.
Um. Can you swim?
Yeah. Kinda--sorta.
Really? Well, in that case.
Do you think maybe you
can teach me how to do it?
You mean.
You don't know how to?
No, 'cause none of the
schools I've attended
ever offered
swimming lessons.
Um, okay sure.
I don't mind teaching you,
but why do you want to
learn all of a sudden?
Geez, you really are a
dumb blonde, aren't you?
Now that I'm friends
with Natsumi,
how awkward is it gonna be
if we go to a pool or a beach
and I don't know
how to swim?
But she's not real.
You can teach me at Sea God's
Palace Land this Sunday.
Sure. All right then.
Let's get one
thing straight.
Don't you dare tell Yozora
I don't know how to swim.
You understand me?
Isn't Udders coming
to the club today?
No, she said she had
some shopping to do.
For what? Some kind
of milking device?
Don't you dare tell Yozora
I don't know how to swim.
-Hey is something on your mind?
-No.
Is that the new book
you were talking about?
It sure is.
Any good?
So far.
You're ten minutes late!
Uh. Sorry!
Sorry for the wait.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just need a cold shower.
Here.
I don't need
help getting in.
Okay, first you're gonna try
to open your eyes underwater.
Hey, gimme some credit!
I can't swim, but I
can at least do that!
-See?
-I gotcha.
Then let's move onto
the harder stuff, okay?
Too bad.
I almost had you that time.
I've gotta admit, swimming is
a lot easier than I thought!
Man, she sure
learns quick!
Here ya go.
Thanks a lot.
And thanks so much for giving
me swimming lessons today!
If Natsumi and I
ever go swimming,
now I'll know what to do.
Yeah, like that'll
happen in the real world.
This place sure is swanky
for a water park, isn't it?
Yeah, but it's on the
verge of bankruptcy.
Are you serious?
Look around -- there's
hardly anybody here.
The last time the
mayor came over,
he and Daddy
were wondering
how much longer this
place could last.
"Daddy?"
Oh, you mean the president
of Saint Chronica's.
Yep.
Speaking of your Dad,
I haven't had a chance
to meet the guy.
I need to stop by some
time and pay my respects.
Wait! Why on Earth
would you want to pay your
respects to my father?
Do you mean to tell me
you think that today
is an actual date
you and I are on?
And you want to meet Daddy
to get his permission to
officially start dating me?
I'm sorry to
burst your bubble,
but I want to meet him
'cause he did me a favor
since he and my
dad are old friends.
I'd like to drop
by to thank him
for helping me with
the admission process
to get into the academy.
Huh?
Well. You should have said so
in the first place, you jackass!
Hey, you're the one whose
imagination ran wild.
Come on, admit it.
What you said was
really suggestive.
Geez, Meat.
'Scuse me?
Um, well.
What I meant to
say was "Geez,
the meat in these fried
noodles is so tender.
"I don't think that
is what you meant.
You're just a little
hyper--sensitive
whenever the word
"meat" is mentioned.
Can you blame me?
I have been since Hozora
started calling me that!
If it bugs you so much,
then why do you answer
whenever anybody says the word?
'Cause it's the first time
anyone gave me a nickname.
Oh?
So getting one actually
made me a little happy.
-Whoa, for real?
-Yes.
But don't ever tell
Yozora I said that!
Now if you're finally
done stuffing your face,
let's get back to my
swimming lessons, okay?
Just give me a minute.
If I was her, I'd be pissed
if someone called me "Meat,"
but a nickname does
make you feel special.
Taka! Hey, Taka!
With you?
No way!
Stuck--up bitch!
Yeah, right!
I won't go out with you
so I'm a bitch, huh?
Well, I'd much
rather be a bitch
than date the three
of you losers!
-You slut!
-Aw, crap, here we go.
Oh, so I'm a
bitch and a slut!
If that's how
you closet cases
talk to all the girls
who turn you down.
Then maybe you dorks
should just date each other!
Watch your mouth,
slut face!
Hey. Check it out, bros!
This chick's shakin'
like a leaf!
Yeah, totally!
Aw, you're scared
of us, ain't ya?
No! I'm not shaking
'cause I'm afraid.
I'm shaking 'cause
I'm angry, jerk!
Sena!
Kodaka!
What do you want, brah?
The girl you're messing
with is with me.
Oh. We had no idea, dude.
She never mentioned
a boyfriend. Tease.
Hey, wait a minute!
You creeps
aren't getting away
with calling me bitch,
slut, and tease!
So get down on your
knees and beg and grovel
for my forgiveness now!
You heard me,
pissants; do it!
Like hell we will!
Violence is
never the answer.
Let go of my hand!
Yeah, douche!
Ow--ow--ow--ow--ow!
Take my advice and just
walk away from this, guys.
Okay?
Uh. Sure thing.
Good choice, boys;
I'm glad we could agree.
-You okay?
-That dude was psycho.
Nice work badass.
You can lick my feet as
a reward if you'd like to.
You sure showed
those guys.
Sheesh, what a bunch
of morons, right?
There was only one moron
here and that was you!
Me? How do you mean?
Why did you have to keep
pushing it with those guys?
They were leaving, but you
just couldn't shut the hell up!
What? Like they
didn't have it coming?
Why are you giving me a
lecture anyway? Rude much?
Because you need a
lecture right now!
There are lots
of guys out there
who're even nastier
than they were!
You could have gotten
hurt just then!
I'm not always gonna be
around to protect you, y'know!
Yeah, well, who cares?
I'll protect myself!
You don't have to
worry about me dude!
The way you're acting,
I sure as hell do!
Wow.
You really are
worried about me.
All right then,
I apologize, okay?
From now on, I promise
I'll be more careful.
Great. Thanks.
I think I'm
done for today.
That's the first
time a boy my age
has ever admitted he
was worried about me.
Well. I'll see ya.
Right.
Um, as for today.
Thanks for everything.
We should go again soon.
I'd like to try out that
wave pool next time.
Uh. Yeah, sure.
I wonder what put her
in such a good mood?
Time to take
you down, punk!
Teach the weakling
a lesson, boss!
Talk about déjà vu.
This reminds me of some of
the fights I got in as a kid.
Mortal brother, help me!
Kobato! What's the matter, huh?
It's the bath!
I almost perished in
that infernal thing!
What? How?
The water turned cold!
This wouldn't
have happened
if it had been filled
with warm blood!
Would you put
something on at least?
Oh, the horror!
Why don't you pick on
someone who's not so weak?
Why don't you make me?
Hey! What was that for?
I was trying to
help you, butthole!
You're wrong.
I'll prove I'm not weak!
Then bring it on, blondie!
Don't ignore me!
Jerk!
Get 'em, guys!
Eat this!
After the fight broke up,
me and that kid
actually became friends.
-Taka.
-Huh?
Do you know what my
mom told me one time?
She said that
in first grade.
It's okay if you can't
make one hundred friends.
What matters is if you
can make real friends,
and ones who
mean more to you
than a hundred
different others would.
Even if you only
make one real friend,
that's better than having a
hundred who are just okay.
I feel the same
way your Mom does.
So how 'bout we agree to be
each other's one real friend
for the rest of our lives?
Even if you never
make any others.
I promise I'll be your
real friend forever.
Hey. Why are you getting
so mushy all of a sudden?
You're the one who started
all that real friend stuff.
Sorry, guess I sounded
kinda girly, huh?
I must have dozed off.
"What matters is if you
can make real friends,
and ones who
mean more to you
than a hundred
different others would."
Right.
What?
Kodaka.
You remember?
Wait, what did you say?
Oh, it was nothing!
You were asleep and
just started muttering.
It surprised me.
Sorry about that.
I didn't mean
to scare you.
Hey, where'd Sena go?
Meat already went home.
-And you're still here?
-Yes.
I was reading my book
and lost track of time.
Oh, well.
I've gotta get going.
That kid.
I wonder whatever
happened to him?
Does he still live here?
And his nickname.
What did I call him again?
For the life of me, I
can't seem to remember.
Maybe he's in
the same boat.
After ten years, I'm sure
he doesn't remember me
or what I said, either.
I was just a kid
when I said it,
but is there
even such a thing?
Real friends who
last forever?
[Music]
Hey, Yozora, tell me,
do you know how to swim?
That's a stupid
question, Fun Bags,
'cause I can do everything!
That sucks big--time.
If you said no, I was gonna
offer to teach you how.
Well, as long as you got
down on your knees
and begged me, of course.
Ever since someone gave me
private swimming
lessons recently,
I've really wanted to pass
on what I had learned.
Wait someone
gave you lessons?
Who taught you and your
pontoons how to swim?
Uh! No one; never
mind what I said!
Next. "Underclassmen
Don't Hold Back!"
Underclassmen?
Is the club getting a
new member or something?
How should I know, Boobsy?