Shut up! There's no way;
she so did not do that.
Oh yes she did,
and, girl...
Yeah!
Hurry up! We're
gonna get in trouble
if we're late again!
I know, I'm trying!
So you went ahead
and bought 'em?
Yep! Brand new shoes!
I'm gonna be
super fast today!
Just you wait!
You'll be eating my dust!
Oh, whatever!
Miss Takayama,
please return to the faculty
room as soon as possible.
Yeah, that one made
me cry a lot, too.
Why is he in the library?
You girls are late again!
We're sorry.
Get changed immediately
and start running laps!
Okay.
-And get a better attitude!
-Okay!
So Sena.
Where are you going now?
I did bring that movie
I was talking about
if you wanted to see it.
What's wrong, Sena?
I forgot my gym clothes.
Do you wanna go back to
that same store again?
I was just about to ask
you the same question!
I... I'm so sorry!
-Oh my God, we almost died!
-He is totally the worst!
[Music]
Kyou, you're so exaggerating.
I am totally not!
I'm telling you;
they both almost died
like right there
in the hallway!
Um, no it's not,
like at all!
Who's in there talking?
She must be on a cell
phone or something.
Come on you
always say that.
I know that girl.
She's in my class.
Yozora something.
Mikazuki, I think.
But I've never heard her
laugh like that in class
or, well, ever.
She always looks
pissed as hell.
Kind of like she's
about to murder someone.
I've never really seen
her talk to anybody.
Crazy.
Hold on this is
officially weird.
She's not talking
on the phone at all!
What the hell?
Who's she talking to?
Is there somebody
hiding in there?
A girl talking to
an invisible thing
in an empty classroom at dusk.
You know, this
sounds exactly
like the beginning of a
book I just started reading.
Next, after
various obstacles,
I discover her secret
and ultimately defend her
by fighting and killing
"a thing not of this World".
Then we would, naturally,
uh, Fall in, uh, love.
I guess.
You know what Tomo I think
I do remember that...
Huh?
That's what she
usually looks like.
But she was so cute
when she was laughing.
What do you want?
I... I was just wondering.
Do you, like, see
ghosts and stuff?
What?
Uh, no. cause
ghosts don't exist.
Well then, who have
you been talking to?
You were watching me?
Look. I was having
a conversation
with my best friend ever.
She's made of air okay!
You have an air friend?
What the crap is that?
It's exactly what
I said it was.
You've heard of an "air
guitar" before, haven't you?
She's like that
but cooler.
So let's see.
You pretend someone is
there and talk to them
like they're
talking back to you?
I'm not pretending.
Tomo exists you big jerk.
See she's right
here next to me!
For example Tomo and I were just
talking about this one time
when we went
to a theme park
back when we were
in middle school.
This group of guys was
totally hitting on us
while we were there.
I mean it was ridiculous
so I decided to
pretend one of them
was going to be our hot
new homeroom teacher.
You just said you
were pretending!
Shut up! The point is
it really happened!
Oh really?
How much of it
really happened?
The part where I was
in middle school.
So only ninety--nine percent
of it was a complete lie?
I was hoping the
amusement park
would at least
turn out to be real.
Seriously who
would want to go
to an amusement
park by themself?
You just admitted
you were alone!
Stop! Go ahead
and get over it
because Tomo is
unbelievably adorable.
That chick is
off her rocker.
This cannot end well.
So this is really about
self-- preservation.
What is that look for?
I dunno.
Wouldn't it be a lot
easier for you to just,
you know, make a
real friend instead.
Not an "air" friend
like adorable Tomo.
But an actual
living person.
Yeah well I would
if I could thank you.
Shocking that you can't.
And just who
are you to talk?
You're that new kid
everyone's afraid of,
isn't that right?
I've been at this school
for well over a month now.
I'm hardly a new kid.
What's your name?
It's Kodaka Hasegawa.
It seems to me you have
no right to say anything
about having friends Kodaka.
First name basis already?
So an entire
month has passed
and you still haven't
made a single friend yet.
Wouldn't you say
that's a little pathetic?
Hey! You only
have an air friend!
Where the hell
do you get off?
There's no reason
to be rude to her.
My friend Tomo is
adorable and crazy smart.
And she's also
an amazing athlete
and the absolute
best friend a girl
like me could
ever hope to have!
What's more.
She would never even dream
about stabbing me in the back.
It's not a mystery.
There's nothing else I can do.
I don't know how
to make friends.
Yeah, I'm not really
that great at it either.
Did you not have any
friends at your old school?
Of course I did.
Don't you still
talk to them?
He said he would text me,
but I haven't heard from him.
Maybe you misunderstood
and just like,
thought you were friends.
Maybe shut up.
Fine, then.
You know, if you wanted,
you could try to pay someone
to be friends with you.
No. That's so lame, gah.
Come on. A small
stipend every week
for spending time
together at school.
Like a prostitute?
What is that, a
friend--stitute?
No, it's a basic contract.
Yeah. There's nothing
wrong with a contract!
Or you could just ask
someone to be your friend.
I've seen people do that
on after school specials,
but I don't really get it.
You ask someone
to be friends,
and the moment they agree,
a friendship is suddenly formed.
Even if you'd never spoken
to each other before then.
What if you never even
talk after getting approval?
Can you still consider that
person to be your friend?
Yeah, well I guess
I can't really blame you.
It's not my thing either.
Besides I'm
pretty independent
so it's not like I need
to have any friends.
Right.
Not having friends must be
so hard on that poor girl.
Condescension has to be
my least favorite thing
in the whole world.
Well.
I can understand.
For whatever reason,
people think if you don't
have a lot of friends
there's something
wrong with you.
I don't think
that's true, though.
At least I hope it's not.
I'm perfectly
fine being alone.
Having a few general
acquaintances at school.
Those types of superficial
friends are enough for me.
Yeah, but still.
I have to admit.
It would be nice to
have a real friend.
-What about school clubs?
-No way.
Why's that a bad idea?
Because we're in
our second year.
Club--based friendships
have already been established.
It'd be too embarrassing
to join one now.
Not to mention
completely obvious.
I guess that's true.
If you're only joining
a club to make friends
and not because you
share an interest,
you're only going to
screw with their dynamic.
You'll end up being
the one loser member
with nothing to offer.
Why would they even
want you to join?
She's got a point.
I'd only join a club
to meet people;
I don't really have
any other reason.
And I would hate to bug them
if they were already friends.
That would suck.
That's perfect.
A club!
See you later, Kodaka!
Why my hair looks like this?
Oh, well, my late
mother was English,
so I get it from her.
I, mean. Hey.
It's not really PC,
but have at it.
Thank you.
It was pretty difficult,
but I guess time heals
all wounds, right?
My father decided to
go abroad for work.
I started going to Saint
Chronica's Academy
in Tooyashi then,
but my first day of school,
I took the wrong bus
and ended up getting
there really late.
When I finally arrived
at the academy.
I was on the verge of tears.
Compared to crusading
armies, Saladin's army.
Hello.
I'm, uh.
The transfer student.
Okay. Great!
My name is Kodaka.
Nice to be here!
Oh no, Miss Osada!
Did he just attack her?
Delinquent, much?
-He's new here?
-What's up with his hair?
I forgot my book.
Uh. Here!
Take mine!
Oh, thanks?
By the evening
of my first day.
The whole school
had heard the rumor.
I was a thug who
stole the book
of the poor girl
sitting next to me.
It's been a
month since then.
And I still haven't been
able to redeem myself
for that first day fail.
See you later, Kodaka!
What a weird girl.
I did like that she
said my first name;
I haven't heard
that at school, yet.
Nice!
In equations of
the nth degree.
There will
always be a root.
As a result, the root of n
in this problem would be.
The usual.
What's wrong with her now?
Kodaka. Follow me, please.
Holy crap, she
talked to him.
To that Hasegawa creep?
Oh. Well, give me a second.
Okay, what's going on?
I've gone through all
the formalities and crap.
What are you
talking about?
I created a new club.
Since we can't join a
club that already exists.
Well. It seemed
only logical for me
to go make a new one.
Yeah, I get it.
In a new club, you don't
have to stress out about
making things
awkward for anybody.
So, what kind of club
did you end up making?
The Neighbors Club.
The Neighbors Club?
That's right.
In compliance with
God's instructions
we embrace everyone
as neighbors,
deepen friendships
on a spiritual level,
yada yada yada, work together
and treat everyone
with the kindness
that God would want,
or what not.
Will a club like that
actually get approved, though?
Are you kidding me?
This school is
full of suckers.
Throw in God or
working hard.
They cannot get
enough of that stuff.
Religion is always
an easy sell.
All right, so then what's
this Neighbors Club
actually going to do?
It's gonna help us
make some damn friends.
And, we can avoid getting
a bunch of pity face
from the other students
while we're at it.
We'll load up on as many
shallow acquaintances as we can.
And then keep our
eye out for people
we could tolerate
as real friends.
Interesting plan
of attack, I guess.
Well, good luck.
Why are you wishing
me good luck.
-You're a member too.
-Huh?
You left before I could get the
paperwork to you yesterday,
so I just went ahead and
filled out your registration.
Say "thank you".
You did what?
You are very welcome.
Now, let the club
activities begin!
You know you want to.
Wait. Where are we going?
This is the chapel's
common room.
You sure this is okay
for the club to use?
The club advisor okayed
it that makes it okay.
Okay. And do they
plan on advising us
on how to make some
new friends, too?
Probably not.
The club advisor in
question is Sister Maria.
She doesn't have a lot
of friends herself.
Then why did she
become our advisor?
I get intimidated by people
who look like they
have a lot of friends,
so I decided
to go with her.
You are something else.
I know. We need to
get more members.
What is this?
It's our poster.
We're gonna put 'em up on
bulletin boards all over school.
We are?
But it doesn't
describe anything
about what the club does.
Shows how much you know.
Try looking at it
diagonally, genius.
Diagonally?
Oh, I see.
Friends wanted?
Get it now?
What did you put a
lame joke in there for?
It's not a joke.
Come on; think about it.
Anyone who is always on
the lookout for friends
is bound to see that
message hidden in the poster.
But that's not all.
I tried to draw a scene
from that famous song,
you know the one about
making one hundred friends
and eating rice balls
at the top of Mt. Fuji.
Even if they don't catch
the diagonal sentence,
the drawing should
totally clue them in on
what we're about.
And you're sure
it's not a joke?
Positive.
Let's hang these
bad boys up.
On to the next one.
Hey.
Are you positive you really
wanna be friends with someone
who's desperate enough to
understand this poster?
So your desperation is
fine, but theirs isn't.
Uh, double
standard dot com.
You know that's
not what I meant.
And you know that I
have an actual name.
But you keep calling me
you all the damn time.
It's really starting
to piss me off.
Oh. I'm sorry.
So, is Mikazuki, alright?
Yozora.
You can use my first name.
Fine. I'll call you that.
Yo... Yozor. uh.
C'mon! Don't you
have a nickname
or something easier
for me to say?
I do.
Did.
Look, I'm not going to
tell you what it was Kodaka.
Why not?
Because only.
Only real friends use
nicknames with each other.
I know! I'm late! I'm sorry!
Man, I'm exhausted.
So. I think we should start
regular activities tomorrow.
Yeah, I seriously
doubt anyone's
going to want to join our club
after looking at that poster.
Oh really? Because that sounds
like a new member to me.
What? We just got back
from putting them up!
This is the Neighbors
Club, right?
I'd like to join, please.
Wrong number.
Hey! What? Yozora!
You're right.
We should start now.
That's not it!
She wants to join.
And she's a girl, who
could be your best friend,
which is kind of what you're
looking for, isn't it?
Don't be ridiculous!
Ohmigah, that
blonde in your hair
is totally
showing right now.
You've already met
my best friend,
and her name is
Tomo; remember?
Okay.
Why did you slam
the door in my face?
I said I want to
join your group!
Die Princess! No!
So, you guys know
each other already?
No, we do not.
Her name is Sena Kashiwazaki.
And she is the daughter
of the Academy president.
She's in Class two--three,
and all the boys worship her.
We do not need to be friends
with princess wannabes.
Oh.
Yeah, I've
heard about her.
Of course.
Why is it ya give
a girl blond hair
and huge knockers and guys
fawn all over them?
-It's disgusting.
-What?
I'm not fawning
all over anybody!
Ooh, she's glamorous and
can play sports really well
and makes straight A's.
Sena has been at
the top of the class
since last year in every
freakin' subject.
She can't be that perfect.
There has to be
something wrong with her!
This chick needs
serious therapy.
She is not giving up!
Why are you being
so mean to me?
The only thing
I'm trying to do
is join your
stupid ass club!
If you're here to
spy on us, go away.
I'm not spying on you!
I saw your poster that said you
were looking for some friends.
I want to join because
I want friends too, okay!
Yeah, everybody knows
how perfect I am.
I'm super smart,
really good at sports,
and, obviously,
I'm totes gorgeous.
Only if cow udders
are gorgeous.
Life must be hard for you
having that flat chest.
Oh please it's not
like I'm that flat.
Well, you know what they say
about a pair of tangerines.
You might as well
have nothing.
If I murdered all the women
who had larger breasts than me,
then I would have a relatively
large rack in comparison,
now wouldn't I?
I don't suppose you
would like to become
the glorious first sacrifice
in my lofty plan?
Please stop.
You came here because
you wanted friends, right?
That's right.
What are you
talking about?
You've got guys around
you all the time!
Those are just servants.
I want more than that.
It'd be nice to have
girlfriends for once in my life!
That way, when teams
are formed in class
or when we leave school
for a field trip.
I'll have friends
I can hang out with.
"Oh, come on, you're surrounded
by boys all the time.
Why don't you hang
out with them?"
I don't want to hear anyone
say that to me ever again.
I just want to have
some real friends!
Now that you mention it.
I have heard girls can be
pretty mean to other girls,
especially if they're pretty,
and popular, and intelligent.
Considering you're a thug,
you're a lot smarter
than I thought you'd be.
I don't mind stepping
on you if you want me to.
What the hell's
wrong with you?
Why would I want
you to do that?
I dunno; the boys in
my class usually love it.
Don't tell me you're looking
for something more than that?
What a pervie creep!
I am not a stupid thug
or a pervie creep!
What the crap
are you looking at?
You. This situation is
perfect for you guys.
With both of you here,
you can make friends
with each other, yeah?
What?
Whatever; why would
I ever, like ever,
want to be friends
with somebody like her.
And why would
I ever, like ever
wanna be friends
with someone like her?
What do you mean
by that, boob face?
They just met?
How can they hate each
other so much already?
So, you wanna
stop and get food?
You know I do;
the usual!!
Please go die.
No, you please go die!
Actually, just get
out of here, like now.
No. I'm joining this club.
You'll just have
to deal with it.
No you're not!
Get out!
No, you get out!
So there!
This is the first day
of the Neighbors Club.
One person joined
bringing us
to a grand total
of three members.
I guess most people would
consider that a smooth start.
Most people
would be wrong.
Hey, I rented this
awesome movie yesterday.
Ohmigah, it was
so hilarious!
Which one was it?
I can't remember the name.
You know the one
where the girl thinks
these people are her friends,
but they're like,
totally the opposite.
[Music]
And these two continued.
You know, you are
a terrible person.
Well, that's better
than being an idiot.
Hello, I'm at the
top of our class!
Oh, someone give
her a trophy.
Lady Meat actually
knows how to study.
You bitch! I can have
my Daddy expel you!
Aren't you a
little embarrassed
to still be using the
word Daddy at your age?
You need to
quit this club.
I can't quit my own club.
Since when was it
just your club?
Next. There's No God
in the Electric World!
Look. They agreed on something.