Maria's a teacher,
but she's not smart
enough to know
that eating junk food's
bad for your health.
That's all she ever eats.
She's gonna make
herself sick.
It's not like we're the poster
children for health food.
Sorry, what was that?
As you know, you're
fortunate enough
to travel in the company
of the great night tribe.
If you keep spending
your time hanging around
an agent of the evil Church,
I promise you,
it'll end in disaster.
Since my other half
is already awake.
I figured it
was only right
that I got out
of bed as well,
plus I'm starving.
Good timing then.
Hmm. Looks like you've put
together quite the feast
this morning, haven't you?
It's not all for
breakfast actually.
Some of it's for lunch.
Well, well. Cooking
multiple meals?
What have you
done with my bro?
Have you finally recognized
how awesome I am
and decided to pay me the
respect I'm clearly owed?
I already told you
this yesterday.
That Maria girl
doesn't eat real food,
all she ever eats is junk.
So I thought I'd help out
by making her a decent meal.
But don't worry.
I made enough
for you, too.
So Maria's the priority
and I'm stuck here
playing second fiddle.
Wha'd you say?
What do you care?
Hey, where are you
running off to?
Your food'll get cold. Kobato!
My brother's dumb. Big time.
[Music]
"This time, the SAGA is
a Serious Battle"
Hey! Didn't expect
to see you so early!
Not again.
A person can't survive
on potato chips alone.
Speak for yourself!
These taste way better
than any of the other stuff
they have here.
Check it out!
Woah.
That's a lotta chips.
Yozora lets me stock
up when I work for her.
You're like a pack rat.
Guess I shouldn't
be surprised.
Here.
Oh wow.
Did you make all
this just for me?
That's very nice
of you, but--
What's your angle, Kodaka?
People don't
just make food.
I don't have
an "angle", okay?
Just make sure
you return my box.
I'll make your lunch
for you tomorrow, too.
Wow.
You're really
being nice to me
outta the goodness
of your heart?
You must be some
kinda saint.
I don't know what it
is, it's just that
you sorta remind me of my
sister when she was little.
I wanna look out for you.
I didn't know you actually
had a younger sister.
I guess it makes sense,
you are the big brother type.
Yeah, well.
I'd love to hang out,
but I gotta get to class.
Lay off the potato
chips, all right?
Okay, big bro! You got it!
Big bro?
I've heard a lot of rumors
about his dining habits.
Apparently, he always eats
his lunch before lunchtime.
Please accept
my apologies.
I'm so sorry my snack
didn't satisfy your hunger
That's not it.
But thank you though.
Big brother! Hey!
Guess what?
I ate my lunch and
it was so awesome!
Yozora's yucky potato
chips taste like poo-poo
compared to what you made!
Poop-head Yozora makes
people eat nasty poo-poo chips!
-Oh?
-I was just kidding around!
Your chips are the best!
It's weird to make a young
girl call you big bro!
Do you have some kinda
sexy 'little sister
fetish' or what?
No. And I'm not 'making'
her call me anything.
Kodaka really
is a big brother,
so I figured it would be
the perfect name for him.
Gosh.
Wouldn't it be awesome to
go inside a video game?
Uh, uh I mean, not really!
That was a joke. I
didn't really mean that.
Just wanted to see
the look on your face!
Don't be embarrassed.
Rika may not be able to
get you into that game
but there's one she can.
Rika has a different
game you could play
where you might have
a similar experience.
Are you serious?
How in the world do you
have something like that?
After Rika helped
them develop it.
They let her keep a
copy of the prototype.
Wanna try it out?
Yeah. Of course!
So what? You put this on?
Yep. It's the newest
head mount display
from a game development
company called Largehard
and it hasn't even
been released.
But when it finally is these
things are gonna be huge.
Also included is
the demo version
of this exclusive software.
It's basically the
greatest 3D interactive
fantasy video game
ever created
and it's called,
"Romancing Saga 14!"
Why, Saga?
Because that's the
prefecture they live in.
That's the reason?
It's pitch black!
I can't see a thing!
Be patient, the
software's still loading.
It won't be
much longer now.
Saga. It is the
final frontier.
Ah, that's not cool.
To bring an
end to this world
the reigning governor
of Saga took action.
He summoned the
Prince of Darkness
from another dimension.
In order to
destroy the Earth.
The opening is long,
so Rika will skip it!
Hey! Don't do that,
I was really interested
in the Valhalla Castle!
Sorry, too late!
First you have
to pick a profession
and that'll determine
the specific attributes
of your characters.
Valhalla Castle.
Right. So.
Maybe I'll be this.
Hey, over here!
Oh wow. That's some
outfit you got there!
Rika chose 'gunner' and
this is what it gave her.
You don't look half
bad yourself, Kodaka.
Wish I could see.
You can! Just select 'equipment'
from the main menu
and it'll show you
what you look like.
What the hell is this?
I chose 'wizard', wizards
don't dress like this!
Rika read about this
urban legend that says
if you stay a virgin
until you're thirty,
you automatically
become a wizard.
Rika thinks you look
just about right.
Clearly your character made
it to thirty without doing it.
I don't wanna be
that kind of wizard!
Come on, this is ridiculous;
my guy doesn't even
know any magic!
Rika would guess it is
perhaps an honorary title.
Is this some sick
practical joke?
Hey! What's up
with your outfit?
I wouldn't talk if
I were you. At all.
Wait just a second!
What the hell stupid
outfit is this,
I chose 'blacksmith!'
Now that you mention it,
it does sorta look like that.
Please, it does not!
I don't remember
'blacksmiths' dressing
all slutty like this.
They can call forth
swords using magic.
And cut their
enemy to pieces!
Actually, that sounds
more like a ninja to Rika.
Aww man, I screwed up.
I picked the worst
possible job
with the worst
possible outfit.
Would you quit your
bitching, Meat?
What are you?
I picked 'rose girl' and
look what it did to me.
Looks like the developer
got a little lazy
when he built that one.
But still, check
out your attack prowess
and your magic ability!
They're through the roof!
As long as I'm still
strong, I'm okay.
You really are in love with
that costume, aren't you?
Not really.
Hey you guys. What do
you think about my outfit?
Well, you uh.
You look very strong.
You're a very authentic
looking Samurai.
Hold on a sec.
Sena, Yozora and Yukimura
are obviously the muscle.
And Rika's the long
distance attacker. What am I?
If Rika had to make an educated
guess, you're worthless.
That's not the answer
I was hoping for.
I guess the only thing we're
missing now is a healer.
Don't worry guys, I'm here!
Maria?
You look exactly the same
as you do in real life.
So I'm guessing you're
the healer then?
Yep. I've seen
that look before.
An acolyte of God is
always an Acolyte of God,
no matter what!
Since everybody is
accounted for now,
should we get a move on?
Guys! Check it out!
That's Valhalla Castle.
the Prince of
Darkness lives here.
This mode is a
simulation that ends
after you defeat
the bad guy.
This prince guy can be
beaten in a simulation?
Remember what
you're wearing,
this game kinda blows.
Looks like we've
got company.
What are they, aliens?
They're completely
disgusting.
They look and
smell like poo!
I know them.
They're Dragon Gobies!
Hold on, what the
heck's a Dragon Gobie?
Fish that inhabit the
Ariake Sea in Kyushu.
I used to eat them
when I lived there!
They don't seem
very appetizing.
Of course, to
each his own.
They're Dragon
Gobie Soldiers,
the first of the small fry.
The only reason
they're in the game
is cause they
look like aliens!
Man that's terrible.
I don't care what they
are or why they're here,
let's kill 'em!
No, stop it!
Don't you feel sorry for them,
being treated like monsters
because of
how they look?
Dragon Gobie's may
be weird looking,
but they didn't ask
to be born that way!
Please. Don't hurt them;
just let them go!
You're a very good man.
With a big heart of gold.
When you look
at those fish
you see yourself don't you?
People as good as you.
They're hard to find.
Yeah. you're really
the best Kodaka.
Thanks guys.
Eat this!
Poor little fish!
Why are you killing them?
What did they ever
do to you, huh?
Huh? Come on, they're gross.
Rika knows how you feel.
But we can't move on
till they're toast.
Their deaths will
not be in vain!
They will live
on inside each of us,
as experience points!
Be gone, demon!
It's Samurai Mercy.
How come they aren't
defending themselves?
They're working out a few
kinks in the program;
Rika guesses the developer
forgot to code in
the enemy attack patterns.
Oh.
Poor little fishies.
The game was rigged.
I know they look
super scary.
But really they're
just delicious!
That sound means we've
made it to the next level.
Guess what? My
skills have increased.
And I can do magic now!
Did I get
experience points,
even though I didn't fight?
Everybody did!
Look, I got a skill!
Okay, it says,
"Don't be stupid,
nothing will happen
just from believing.
Nothing changes in reality
unless you take action
instead of just sitting
around like an idiot."
Screw you.
And so we
dispatched a variety
of Dragon Gobie monsters.
And finally arrived
at Valhalla Castle.
Wow, It's so big.
The Prince of
Darkness is a Gobie!
The developer really
phoned it in this time.
Apparently this Prince of
Whatever isn't playing around!
Oh come on, no dialogue
for the main bad guy either?
Bullet-proof!
Sena! Are you okay?
I didn't feel a thing.
The problem is, I lost almost
half of my battle points.
That's why we brought
a healer with us,
where is she?
Maria!
Maria! What's wrong?
Wait a minute, something
isn't right about this!
Yeah, Rika thinks she
fell asleep on the couch.
That girl is
completely useless.
I don't blame her,
the Prince of Darkness
is pretty boring;
I think a nap
sounds really nice.
You guys!
If I use my "Rose Guard"
it will nullify
the enemies slashing attack
making it vulnerable to
a straight on charge!
Well what do you think
Sena are you game?
Oh, I'm all over it!
Blasting hammer!
Here I come!
Do it now!
Yozora!
These wall graphics look
totally realistic don't they?
Hey, what the--
That's gotta hurt.
She's dead.
Hey, don't get mad at me,
all I did was say
I could nullify its
attack in theory.
I never said
I was actually
going to go
through with it.
You told her to
charge it head on!
Only because I knew she
would be stupid enough
-to do it.
-Thanks a lot, jerk!
Why the hell
did you do that?
Huh? Hey. What is this?
Rose Guard!
All right, way to go!
I hope it works before
I run outta juice!
Yukimura, Rika, while I'm
holding this thing off,
circle around and launch
a joint attack from the rear!
-All right!
-Okay, sounds good!
Rose guard!
What's wrong?
Hey. What the--
Yozora, you okay?
Damn you, Meat. Damn you!
Victory is mine!
That's what you get
for underestimating me!
I see.
She tickled her real
body to distract her.
I wanted to die on the
field of battle like a hero.
You're on your
own now, Kodaka.
Don't leave me. You guys!
Well, it looks like this
is the end of the line.
Big bro!
Maria!
Hey when did you wake up?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
-Use your magic to
-Bastard! How dare you?
Messing with my brother
like that was a huge mistake
and I'm gonna make
you pay for it, buddy!
I may look innocent, but
when you mess with my bro,
the gloves come off!
Hey!
I'm talking to you!
That's it.
The end.
Maria?
Kobato. It's you.
This girl said
she would save you
if it's the
last thing she did.
I figured I'd
come check on you.
And, plus I've always
wanted to know
what keeps you out
so late at night.
But I didn't expect it to be
a video game for little kids!
Are you gonna introduce
us to your friend or what?
How do you know this girl?
We're related.
Her name is Kobato, and
she's my little sister.
Come on, there's no way
your little sister
could be this cute!
Hey, that's mean!
So what's going on?
Why did you decide
to come here?
Well, big brother, I'm
glad you asked that.
Lately, you've been
neglecting me
and spending all
your time hanging out
with this bunch
of idiotic mortals.
So I've come here
because it's obvious
you need supervision.
So basically, you're
upset because you feel
your brother has put the club
before your relationship,
so you wanted to drop
by and check it out.
Is that about right?
No. Not at all!
This girl has a
brother complex!
But I can't decide if I
should hate her or not
because she's so
darn adorable!
Please stop going on about
how cute she is, it's creepy.
Listen.
I'm sorry I've been coming
home so late all the time.
I know!
How bout, from now on, I
make some pork bone ramen
every Sunday to
make it up to you?
Are you serious?
You'd do that?
Will you make it with extra
garlic the way I like it?
Sure, why not?
Yay!
Plus, it's my day off,
so I'll be able to get some
serious cooking
done for once.
I can also make
you some lunch.
You're good at that.
Big bro!
Did you defeat the Prince
of Darkness or what?
I'm so glad you're safe!
What's gotten into you,
are you talking in your sleep?
I'm wide-awake now.
That game didn't
last very long.
I'm so sorry, Big Brother,
I wanted to protect you
from danger but I drifted
off during the game!
Shut up!
Dummy!
Jerk face!
Weirdo! You big stupid head!
Haven't you ever heard
it's not nice to call
people names
like that, moron?
Shut up, you idiot!
Who the heck do
you think you are?
It's her.
My sister, Kobato.
Wait a sec, this is
really your little sis?
Would you please
stop calling me that?
I am big.
I have not been
little for years.
Well. Is she your
sister or not?
She's my sister.
He says you are.
I'm a member of the Night Tribe
and have lived among humans
for thousands of years.
My kind has been
at war with you
self-righteous Church dogs
for as long as
I can remember.
They call us 'vampires'
and we strike terror
into the hearts and minds
of people everywhere.
A vampire!
Yes I'm familiar
with your breed!
Tell me, what is a
vampire doing here?
I've come here to keep
my brother away from you.
So his mind isn't poisoned
by a villainous
member of the Church!
On second thought, perhaps
it wouldn't be a bad idea
to join your little club.
You can't, you're
still in middle school.
I don't know of
any rule that prevents
a middle school student
from joining up with a club.
Yeah. Since she's your little
sister, it should be fine.
-Huh?
-She's in.
Plus it seems pretty
clear she has no friends.
Whaddaya say, you
wanna join our club?
The only true friend
I've ever had is
the bitter darkness
of the night.
You're right; she definitely
doesn't have any friends.
Someone wanna tell me why
we're letting a vampire in?
My vote's a definite 'no!'
If you so much as touch
a hair on his head, I swear--
He is an apostle of God
who makes me delicious lunches,
and If I so please, I'll
touch every hair on his head!
Time for you to die!
In the name of all that's
holy, I render judgment on you!
Wrong church lady, you're
the one who will shrink
before my dark magic.
My darkness is so powerful
it once made a school classroom
rip right in half!
How do you like this?
How bout that?
Your power is weak!
I'll show you weak!
Yikes!
Oh boy.
I really do wish
they'd cut it out already!
I mean it,
I said let me go!
What do you think?
Want to clean up?
You know what guys?
I don't think that
game had a point.
What? If you had just watched
out for me back there,
that Prince of Darkness
would have been dead by now.
Well, if you
had been useful
we might have
let you stick around.
What did you
just say to me?
I'm saying you need to
learn a little more skill
They sound like your
sister and Maria.
-Weird.
-Yeah.
They sure do.
I guess the lesson here is
that we shouldn't let them
play video games together.
That's too bad.
Rika had a really
great time!
It was the first time Rika
ever played a game
with other people.
That's the most
fun she's ever had.
You really outta
go to a doctor
and get that checked out.
Ha, ha, ha!
Oh, Yozora!
Rika forgot to tell you your
outfit earlier was so cute!
Rika's totally crushing.
Hey! Don't tell
me that! It's weird!
Rose Girl.
-She's super cute!
-Stop!
I promise you this Jugs,
I'll make you sorry
you ever called me that!
I love you.
My brother really
is a good person.
[Music]
You dirty vampire.
Be gone now!
As a descendant
of the night tribe,
I possess a power
that is far greater
than you could imagine,
you church freak!
Is that right?
You. Are. Stupid!
I told you that won't work
on me, knock it off, kid!
Hey I'm not a kid!
I'm a full-fledged adult!
And I have a lot
of adult knowledge
about lots of adult things!
Yeah? What sorta things?
Like se--
'There Aren't Many Customers
at the Karaoke Box.'
When you're under the
covers with the man you love
and you count the
cracks in the wall
cause you're bored
that's called se--
Be gone, Apostle of God!