Don't you think
it's a little too hot
to be wearing
all of that?
We've gone over
this before.
Heirs of the
Night Tribe
are not affected by heat
the way mortals are.
Oh jeez...!
It's like walking
into a hair dryer!
O' detestable light
of the sun.
You have won
today's battle,
but there shall come a
time when the Night Tribe
will envelope the world
in darkness and then...
no more light.
Right now, I wouldn't
object to that.
[Music]
I'm still alive!
Big Brother.
You must be exhausted.
So nice of you
to join us today.
Yeah, just like I
always do at this time.
It's summer vacation.
Why would you wait until
school would normally be out?
What time did you
guys get here?
About one o' clock.
Meat was already here
being productive...
playing a video game.
She wasn't that far in.
Yozora showed up just
a little after Sena.
So early.
And let me guess.
you were here, too?
I arrived here
at eight AM.
It was very important for
me to be here before you.
I'd rather take my own
life than have you wait.
Don't take this
the wrong way,
but it's not
that big a deal.
I've already
prepared your lunch.
That's sweet; but
I ate before I left.
I'm sorry. And there's
no reason to cook for me
now that school's out.
Does this mean my services
are no longer needed
and you're letting me go?
Heaven help
my heart;
my Big Brother doesn't
need me anymore.
I'm worthless
in his eyes.
I have no choice
but to end it all!
I didn't mean
it like that!
I need you;
I'm just not hungry!
If you're not gonna eat
both of those, can I have one?
I'm starving!
Brilliant timing.
I bet she was expecting me
to bring her something.
Look, you saved the day!
Is it cool if I give
this to Maria instead?
Not that I
wouldn't want it!
I just mean it would help if you
made her lunch instead of me
during the summer
break to save time?
It would not be
appropriate for a samurai
to serve two masters.
I'm sorry.
What is she talking about?
Alright, listen.
It's not serving
two masters.
Maria's like a
sister to me.
So you'd be doing a noble
service for your master
if you looked after
her, wouldn't you?
Yes I would.
You're right!
I would actually consider
it a great honor, Sir.
You mean it?
You see me as your
little sister?
Miss Maria.
My Big Brother
has requested
that I prepare
your meals for you.
And so, I will now
be at your service.
I know! Isn't it great?!
You got all this stuff
from the convenience store!
Oh! Look how much
sugar's in 'em!
-Yum!
-Yeah.
This isn't the healthiest
meal you could've brought me.
You're such a
strong, healthy man;
I knew you
could handle it.
Plus, you deserved a break.
Thank you. Let's say
from here on out
you prepare only nutritious
meals for Maria, okay?
I understand.
As you wish.
What's the point in
learning good behavior
if you're just going to
give the reward away?
See you later.
Have a good day.
Oh man. Made it.
Good to see you.
Looks like you've already
been working hard.
Hi, where is everyone?
I don't know.
They're not here, yet.
Miss Maria came by
for a little while
and then remembered she had
some sisterly duties to tend to.
So she went home.
Okay. Did you
bring her lunch?
Yes. I made sure
it was healthy
just as you instructed.
Very rich in vitamins
and calcium...
and protein.
How many protein
shakes did she drink?
It wasn't easy to
tell you the truth.
She resisted but
they were your orders,
so I had no choice
but to force them down.
Tell me you're joking.
It reminded me a
little of that story
we learned in history class
about the execution
of Manpukumaru.
Manpuku-who?
Maru. He was only ten
when his parents abandoned him,
thinking he'd be safe
from the evil rulers.
Instead, he was
found and beheaded.
I bet the way that
little boy screamed
when he met his
death sounded
just like poor Maria.
What do you
mean screamed.
Please, tell me
what happened.
She resisted;
but they were your orders,
so I had no choice but
to force them down.
Your orders...
your orders...
your orders.
Alright, starting tomorrow
see if you can make something
that's both nutritious
and tastes good
to a ten-year-old.
I don't need any more
Man-puke-a-roo incidents here.
Right. Your wish
is my command.
They ever gonna show up?
You've had such a long
day, Big Brother.
You're all here,
of course.
Why didn't any of
you come yesterday?
Poor Kodaka!
Were you feeling lonely
by yourself without Rika?
'Lonely' is not exactly
the word I would use.
Sorry, Kodaka, something
suddenly came up.
Yeah and I was too busy
being jerked around.
How so?
I thought the game
was almost over,
so I was just going to
finish it and then leave.
But as it turns out, I actually
had four more hours to go!
Way longer than
I expected!
I didn't even notice
what time it was
because I was lost
on the journey!
When Mikane finally met
her prince at the end,
it was so beautiful
I couldn't move!
You were playing
a video game.
It's more than
just a game!
You can borrow it,
you'll see!
It's a life-changing
experience!
When you finish, you
have to start it over!
The ending changes the entire
meaning of the beginning
and the whole journey!
Just like real life! It's about
how we're all on a path...
I just thought
of something!
What?
Let's come up with a way
that we can let each other know
what time we're all
going to be here
and if we can
make it or not.
I think you may be on
to something there.
I'm surprised that came
out of you, Kodaka.
but, now that it has,
how do we do it?
I was thinking...
maybe like an internet
group or something?
You're crazy!
You won't even
consider it?
I try to use the internet
as little as possible.
Online shopping and research
are about it for me.
Okay, but why?
I did something
recently...
and I don't want
to be recognized.
I'm not even gonna ask
what that's about.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, I had a pretty crappy
experience with message boards
so I'm not interested
in being found online.
Ugh! Just thinking about
it pisses me off.
I could kill those ugly trolls
for the way they treated me!
They will never be forgiven
for the things they said!
What happened?
Did you get in a fight?
I was harassed!
They were calling Natsumi a
heartless, lobotomized hooker
just because of
the way she looks!
And I was not gonna
let that slide!
I told them looks
aren't everything
and she's actually very nice
once you get to know her.
And how well do
you 'know' her?
Well enough that talking
crap about her around me
is pretty much a
declaration of war!
They can either
admit they were wrong
and apologize to me...
or we can fight it out
and determine who's right
the old-fashioned way!
So what you're saying is
message boards aren't
gonna work for you, right?
Oh I know...
How about setting up a page
for a private group on Nixi?
What are you doing
on Nixi, Kodaka?
And why haven't
you added me?
'Cause I'm not on it,
that's why.
-You know it?
-Yeah.
You're a member,
aren't you?
Of course not! Why would
I put myself out there
for all those stalkers?
Yeah. I agree.
Rika's not a member
yet, either.
Turns out it's not the
easiest site to join.
You have to actually
know someone
and have them add you
to their contact list.
So since none
of us are members,
we couldn't join
if we wanted to.
Nixi isn't the only social
networking site though.
There must be
something private
that doesn't require
an invitation.
Rika has a suggestion.
Why don't we just
exchange phone numbers
and use text messaging?
Texting.
You mean send messages
with our cell phones?
Yeah... that's
what it is, right?
I guess. I mean,
I forget sometimes
I can text people
besides my sister.
Rika, you are a genius!
Text messaging.
I never even thought
about that.
The only other thing I used
on my phone was the GPS
and some karaoke
apps I downloaded.
That does it.
Rika, you leave me
no other option
but to agree that
you are a genius.
Rika is very thankful
for the compliments.
Okay, great,
let's do this!
Who's ready to exchange
numbers with Rika?
I am!
'Kay. Here it is.
I'll go get mine!
Come on...
here it is!
This is my cellular
telephone!
The numbers don't just jump
in there by themselves.
Oh yeah, that's
a good point.
Rika's never seen
one like this!
It's so pretty!
The color almost glows!
Thank you?
Rika sent a group text.
Did you all get it?
You messaged all of us?
I don't have anything.
You sure you sent it?
I didn't get
anything either.
Maybe my phone
doesn't get them?
Or maybe you have to send
it to me separately.
Where would
I look for it?
Which picture
do I click on?
I'm not seeing anything.
Rika you might have to
send it to me again.
This sucks... I must've
freaking deleted it or something
'cause it's not in here!
I got it.
How did you do that?
Just reply back and
we'll all have yours.
There it is!
Rika has your
address now.
And look, it comes
with a picture too!
What's happening?
Why am I having a hard
time figuring this out.
Why's it so easy for them?
Because... they're
from the future.
Kids these days.
They're much
more advanced.
It's true.
They're growing up in a
new virtual generation...
they live their
entire lives
just like video games
with digital controls.
Somehow a stupid
smart phone
made us 'generations'
ahead of them.
People like Big Brother
who are used to doing
things without technology
have a hard time
understanding why it's useful
and sometimes
feel threatened.
How is it that you're
so well versed
in the ways of
text messaging?
Why didn't you tell
me about this before?
This is dumb.
It doesn't make sense!
And it doesn't make
sense for someone
who doesn't have any friends
to use a feature like this!
Screw it! I'm just going to type
in your number the normal way
so tell me what it is!
I was just thinking
the exact same thing!
This is way
too much work!
Here, just copy
it off my screen.
I'm almost done.
Why is your stupid
number so freaking long?
Um. I don't think you
have to type in the dashes.
'Kay. Then how am I
supposed to type it?
There! I did it!
Great!
I think I'm
gonna try it.
You ready?
I'm about to send
a text message.
Yeah. Go.
I think I got it!
Are you sure?
I mean I did!
This is you, right?
Great. So now I just
have to save your number.
Y... O... Z-O... R... A... save.
Sweet! It worked!
Another contact in my
phone besides my family!
Hey, this actually
feels kinda cool
seeing your
name in there.
Are you serious?
You don't have numbers of
friends from other schools?
No, is that bad?
It's not like I
didn't have friends,
we just always said we'd
exchange numbers when I left
and then we never did.
I guess that makes me
kind of a crappy guy, huh?
Maybe.
But on the bright side
now I get to be your
very first phone-friend.
And you get to be my very
first phone-anything.
I don't even have my
family's numbers saved!
This is a big
deal Kodaka!
Wow, I'm so honored!
Rika was starting
to feel really guilty
about not giving better
instructions on texting.
But seeing
them so elated
after figuring it
out on their own
makes Rika think it
worked out for the best.
Whatever!
It's just a
stupid cell phone!
What's the big deal?
Why are you so angry?
What makes you
think I'm angry?
I don't know.
My mistake.
Hey, what's your number?
I'll type it in now
that I know how!
I don't have one.
What?
I don't have a stupid
cell phone, okay?!
And I don't
want one!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that.
Don't be sorry!
I said I don't want one.
They're just props for all the
stupid giggly bimbos in my class
who need to feel like
they're important.
I'm way too busy being
organically awesome
to worry about that!
Well, there are certainly
more people in this world
who don't have a cell
phone than those who do.
And we manage just
fine, thank you.
I'd even be okay if I
didn't have a home phone...
but then I'd be depriving
way too many people
of hearing this goddess's
voice in their ear,
and nobody should miss
out on that miracle.
We're all thankful
for your mercy.
-Hello?
-It's me.
Just wanted to double check
if you saved my number.
Yeah, it's still in there.
Come back! I mean, as long
as we're on the phone,
let's talk!
But, you're right there.
It's different
on the phone.
I can ask phone-call
questions.
So, what did you have
for dinner last night?
I don't know.
It was good, though.
Really?! That's
what you're going to
talk about on a cell phone?
Who cares what you
had for dinner?!
Keep your voice
down, Meat.
Can't you see
we're on the phone?
I don't want to have to talk
all over your squawking.
Now run along and do
something, Jiggly.
This is really
convenient, too.
Now we can talk to each
other about whatever we want
even if we're not
in the same room.
Then why don't you guys go
somewhere and demonstrate!
I'll give you a call
when I'm about to leave
so you'll know
when I'll be here.
We'll figure out how to group
text and use that to plan
and discuss all
the club activities.
I forgot to mention that I went
to a great restaurant last night
and ordered... meat...
I had a really amazing
curry with chicken... meat...
if you're wondering
how the... meat... was,
I'd say it was quite
tender and delicious.
What are you talking
about over there?
Meat, this has nothing
to do with you.
I'm talking about the
restaurant's... meat...
chicken... meat...
not the pig... meat...
but... meat...
that was marinated
perfectly in my curry...
I don't know how they meet the
demand for their meat dishes.
Meat is usually
so expensive.
Stop talking
about "meat!"
Shut, up you
stupid idiot!
You're such
a jerk!
Meat has some lungs
in there doesn't she?
As if you weren't
expecting that.
Your talent for
pressing Sena's buttons
is both sick and impressive.
How's it going?
My friend, The Night
has brought you home.
Yup. I'm gonna make dinner.
You hungry?
In one click my
contacts have doubled.
Who could be calling
at this hour?
Uh, hello?!
Someone just
trying to prank me?
Hello?
-Anyone there?
-Um hi.
Yes, my name is Sena.
and uh, I'm looking
for Kodaka.
I mean, is Kodaka there?
-Sena, are you okay?
-Yeah.
-Um, is this Kodaka?
-Yes.
What's wrong with
you, Creepy Pants?!
That scared the
crap out of me!
Why'd you change your
voice like a Psycho-tron?!
Are you trying
to trick me?!
It's how I sound
when I'm half asleep.
Do you have any idea
what time it is?
I don't have time to discuss
your vocal acrobatics right now.
Which cell phone
do you have?
The one I've always had.
And which one is that?
What brand?
Style? Do you like it?
Why? Don't be a smarty!
Oh.
Well, the company
is Turn-AU.
I don't know what the
model is, though.
Well go look.
I'll wait.
-What?
-Hurry up!
Alright,
it's an M61B.
-Turn-AU M61B?
-That's right.
Okay, got it.
Talk to you later.
What the hell was
that all about?
Completely naked and
waiting for you, Kodaka.
You just imagined Rika
naked, didn't you?
You are such a
dirty pervie!
Guess that means
you'd want to know
that Yozora's wearing
a flesh suit, too!
Here's a picture of her
perfectly soft and round
patootie to prove it!
Hope you enjoy!
I'm wearing clothes,
and that was Rika's arm.
Oh yeah!
Yozora, stop!
Why are you pulling down
Rika's undies like that?!
No, Rika can't
pose like this!
It's too embarrassing!
Kodaka you need
to be careful.
That one's
a pervert.
Good to see you!
Rika just discovered how great
the girl-on-girl stories are!
Rika never thought
about it before,
but loves all
sexcapades!
They say it's good to
have passions in life.
You want some tea?
Sure, thanks.
Where is everyone?
Oh. They all had things
to do so they left.
It's kinda late.
We should get home, too.
Yeah.
The goddess has
descended upon you!
Great. Thanks.
-I'm going to sleep.
-What?!
Really?! That's all
you have to say?!
Fine, let's see how
apathetic you are
when you see
this sexy guy!
You're speechless,
aren't you?
I decided to go ahead and
ask Daddy for one yesterday
and he bought
it for me.
That's, the exact same
cell phone that I have.
Even the color!
Is it?
What a strange and
unplanned coincidence.
There's no way
that's a coincidence.
You are so pathetic
sometimes.
Now we can text each other
and have inside jokes, too!
Quick, get
your phone out!
'Kay. Do you know
how to send a text
so that I can
save your number?
Of course I do!
Don't act like you didn't
just learn how yesterday!
I wasn't!
Don't be jealous.
I'll let you text me, too.
Here's my number.
I have absolutely no
desire to text you.
What?! Not even for the club?!
Then why did I buy
this stupid thing?!
So that you can
stalk me, apparently.
Please, no one wants
to deal with you
more than
they have to.
I was just trying to
be a good club mate.
Not my fault if I
send something out
and you're
completely lost
because you were being
a Droopy McDrooper.
I wanted to save you
some embarrassment.
The least you can
do is thank me! Gah!
Thank you, but
I'm fine...
I'll find another
way to keep up.
We already tried other
ways to keep up!
Aww.
Are we throwing
a temper tantrum?
That's not the way to get
what you want from me.
Try being a little more
grown-up and sincere.
What are you saying?
If you think I'm going to
beg you, you're crazy!
You know what?!
Forget it!
I don't want your
smelly number!
She's way too
soft for real.
It's Sena.
I need you to give me that
Horned Beast's number.
She's gone too far.
I need to get her back.
This is what she says in
her first text message?
I'm not surprised.
If she wants my number that
badly, I'll give it to her.
But I need hers first.
What is it, Kodaka?
Tell me so I can give
her what she wants.
Um. Okay.
Help! I don't
know what to do!
This is so awful!
Please! Can you tell
me what happened?!
It won't stop!
I've tried everything!
Whoa... what is that?
So weird!
I think
it's broken!
I think I'm gonna
call it a night.
Kodaka, do something!
Well, let me see it.
What am I going to do
if it can't be fixed?
It was my first
cell phone!
It'll be okay.
We'll fix it.
See! It's already
looking better!
I bet if you smile, it'll
heal the rest of the way.
Maybe?
[Music]
Meat, I think everyone these
days has a smart phone.
Smart phone...?
Oh! I've heard of those!
Yeah. They're super
efficient and easy to use,
but only under one condition:
You have to be
smart to own one.
So I guess you're out of
luck there, Fatty Cakes.
-Really?!
-No, not 'really'.
But my god, you're dense!
What?! I believed you there
for a second, you turd!
But now that I think about it,
it really doesn't
make any sense at all.
There's nothing this
Goddess can't use!
Next time--School
Swimsuits Don't Appear!
What?! Swimsuit episode?!
Why do guys love
swimsuits so much?
It just looks
like wet underwear!