Oh.
Thank you, Kodaka;
that was really nice of you.
Now if you'll excuse me.
Y'know what; hold on a sec.
Let me get one.
I appreciate that, Kodaka.
You're very welcome, Aoi.
I guess you can go ahead
and follow me this way
if you want to.
[KODAKA]
Carrying two boxes this heavy
at once makes it seem like
you want them to fall.
[AOI] I don't; I'm just
trying to make up time
on my student council work
since I skipped it for a week.
[KODAKA]
You skipped for a week?
Hey, do you mind telling me
why you were so set on
destroying the Neighbors Club?
Because Sena is
exceptionally gifted.
And she should be somewhere
appropriate for her gifts.
What do you mean
somewhere appropriate?
Face it.
Sena Kashiwazaki is
unbelievably talented
and needed a better way
to make use of those talents.
Your club was just
a waste of her time.
Wow.
So then, you tried to
disband the Neighbors Club
for the sake of your
so-called mortal enemy?
Yes.
If you say so.
[KODAKA]
I guess she has a point.
Sena would be an asset to
any club she decided to join.
It's not just her, either.
Yozora and Rika have that super
smart thing going on for them.
And then you have Yukimura and
Kobato, who are both popular.
Maybe Aoi's right.
Maybe there's really no point to
even having the Neighbors Club.
[AOI]
No, I'm just kidding.
You what?
I don't like Sena.
She gets everything her
little heart desires, so I just
wanted her to realize she
might lose something one day.
So in other words,
I'm wicked jealous of her.
Well, the funny thing
is you're wrong;
she doesn't have everything.
Yeah?
What doesn't she have?
She doesn't have friends.
Jeez, are you okay?
[AOI laughing]
[KODAKA]
Why are you laughing?
I forgot you have such
a great sense of humor.
You're hilarious,
you know that?
I'm not falling for it, though;
there's not a single person
in the whole world
who doesn't have friends.
[AOI]
I wouldn't be so sure.
It was really sweet of you
to try and cheer me up
after what I did.
Thank you again, Kodaka.
[AOI]
Almost--There.
You were a big help.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
You still have more, yeah?
I can help you with those.
[AOI]
No, I can't ask you to do that.
[KODAKA] This stuff got piled up
because of the Neighbors Club.
So I'm partly to blame;
I can't not help you.
Don't you need to go meet
with that club, though?
Well, we're not really big on
planning activities every day.
So if we have other stuff to
do first, it's not a big deal.
[KODAKA] Why do I feel like
I have to make excuses?
Weird.
[KODAKA] Well on the bright
side, we made it halfway.
[AOI]
I guess so.
[GIRL laughing]
[HINATA] Well, you two seem
to be working well together.
[AOI]
Hinata.
What did you come out here for?
I heard some extremely
nice individual started
helping you with your chores.
I thought I'd come check
on you and thank him myself.
Oh.
Uh, hello.
I'm Kodaka Hasegawa
from class Two-Five.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, it's totally you.
[AOI]
Wait, you know who he is?
Nope.
No clue.
[AOI] Then what the heck
was that reaction about?
I dunno.
Call it a whim.
I'm Hinata,
the student council president.
It's nice to meet you.
Yeah.
Cool.
Hey, I was wondering,
why are you helping Aoi?
This is a lot of work.
You guys must be like
dating or something, yeah?
No!
We're not dating.
Besides, Kodaka probably
already has a girlfriend.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Um, no.
Come on, you're telling me
that you're not dating anyone
from the Neighbors Club?
No, I am not.
It just isn't like that
with them, okay.
[AOI]
Hm.
Prob'ly for the best.
[KODAKA]
What do you mean?
What's for the best?
Well, if you think about it,
you're the only boy
in the whole club, so
you're surrounded by girls.
If you dated one of them,
the whole atmosphere
would get like way awkward.
Yeah.
That's for sure.
So.
If you're not her boyfriend,
why are you helping out?
Because he happens to be
one of those guys who
comes to the rescue when
he sees someone in trouble.
Oh my.
Well isn't that fancy.
[HINATA]
Keep up the good work, kid!
[KODAKA]
Okay, I think that's it.
For the last time,
thanks so much for your help.
Don't worry about it;
it's not a problem.
See ya later.
Oh hey, uh Kodaka.
Yeah?
You seem like
you're a cool guy.
Wanna join the
student council with us?
We just lost our general
affairs person, so we're
looking for a replacement,
if you're interested.
You should definitely join;
it'll be a ton of fun;
I promise.
Really?
I'm surprised you'd
wanna work with me.
Actually, the council only
has girls on it right now.
I think it would be nice
for us to have a guy around.
Honestly, Kodaka, you would be
perfect on the student council.
I don't know.
Haven't you heard the way
people talk about me?
I don't want to
bring you guys down.
I don't get it.
What's wrong with a super-cool,
bad-boy chic, real life haver?
Yeah, thank you,
but you're the only one
who thinks that about me.
See, most people
don't think I'm bad-boy chic,
they assume I'm just bad.
I get called a delinquent
and all sorts of mean things.
It's cuz I have weird hair
and a grumpy face.
[HINATA]
That's true.
Your hair does get attention,
and you have evil looking eyes.
There, you see?
Putting me on the
student council would
wreck your reputation,
and I don't want to do that.
Only fools
judge on appearances,
and I simply don't
care what fools think.
Are you gonna let idiots decide
what you can and can't do?
What's the matter, Kodaka?
You look a little dazed.
[KODAKA]
No.
I mean, yes; I'm fine.
Good to hear.
So, are you gonna join?
No.
No, I'm sorry.
I think the
student council might be
a little too much for me.
But, if all you need is more
manual labor, just let me know.
I'd be happy to help out
whenever and wherever I can.
Plus, I'm almost always free.
Really?
The library asked for us
to help with a project,
so if you'd like
to come by tomorrow,
that would be so great.
Sure.
Count on me to be there.
That's the perfect answer!
[KODAKA]
A week went by so fast,
I barely even realized
what was happening.
I ended up helping the student
council pretty much every day.
It's kind of funny.
All the kids at school think
Hinata is like a god for
"getting that punk in line".
She's getting even
more popular than before.
My reputation's
the same, though.
No surprise, there.
I haven't set foot into
our clubroom since then.
Don't get me wrong,
the Neighbors Club
still means a lot to me.
But after running out on them
like that, I couldn't go back.
I don't know why;
I just couldn't.
[YUKIMURA]
Look who I finally found.
[KODAKA]
Yukimura.
Big Brother.
[KODAKA]
Oh.
Hey, Yukimura.
What's up?
I heard a despicable
gang captured you,
and that they were forcing
you to do manual labor.
So I have come to your rescue.
You know, that's
really rude to say.
Kodaka's helping us
because he's nice,
and that's all there is to it.
Seriously?
Is that the truth, Brother?
Yeah.
[YUKIMURA] In that case,
I shall help out as well.
[AOI]
No, thanks!
And besides, why would you?
Aren't you the one
who wanted to poison me?
I am.
Why are you wearing
a boys' uniform, anyway?
I'm wearing this uniform
because I am endeavoring
to become a true man.
You wanna be a true man?
What does that even mean?
[YUKIMURA] It means I want
to be a great man.
What?
You do realize
you're a girl, don't you?
That is of no importance.
True and genuine men can
transcend their birth gender.
Have you just been let
out of an insane asylum?
Cuz ya sound kinda crazy.
[YUKIMURA]
Big Brother.
May I slay that
villain, please?
You may not slay
student council members!
I'm sorry, Aoi.
But will you excuse us
for a minute?
Sure.
If that's what you really want.
So, tell me.
Anything new at
the Neighbors Club?
No.
Sena is still totally engrossed
with those video games
about making friends
with girls and stuff.
Man, she just won't
give up on those, will she?
How is everyone else doing?
[YUKIMURA]
I'm not sure.
Yozora and Rika haven't been to
the clubroom for a few days now.
Maria comes by to have
a snack now and again,
but after that, she leaves.
[KODAKA] So you and
Sena are the only ones
who are showing up anymore?
[YUKIMURA]
Yes.
We're it, I'm afraid.
[KODAKA]
Oh, great.
What am I supposed
to do about this?
[YUKIMURA] Big Brother,
I can carry half of these.
[KODAKA]
No, they're not heavy.
I'm fine.
[YUKIMURA] Then, is there
any other way I can
be of service to you?
Nah, not today.
Thank you, though.
Yes, I understand.
[YUKIMURA]
I shall come back tomorrow.
[KODAKA]
Hey, Yukimura?
I don't understand why
you're always looking
for some reason to serve me.
You are my sworn brother,
I enjoy helping you when I can.
[KODAKA]
Then let me ask you this.
Yes?
[KODAKA] Why on Earth
would anyone still want
to be my sworn brother.
I mean, come on.
You've gotta realize
the truth by now.
I'm not this genuine man
that you want to be;
I'm just pathetic.
I'm just a big,
fat, stupid wimp.
[YUKIMURA]
I know.
What the--?
You agree?
[YUKIMURA] As I said before,
I am your sworn brother.
[KODAKA]
Okay.
Then explain why you haven't
disowned me already!
Seriously, what is
the point to all this?
Does there really have to
be a point, Big Brother?
I serve you.
Because I want
to be by your side.
What other reason
do I need, right?
What would you do if, um, if
the club was, um, disbanded?
I would be sad, of course.
But I would be here.
I will continue to
serve you no matter what.
You're a really cool
person, you know that?
The fact is you're
too good to me.
Hopefully, one day
I'll be worthy enough
to be your big brother.
[YUKIMURA]
Kodaka.
Oh, Big Brother.
Never in my life have I been
so frustrated I'm not a boy!
It's one of the
worst feelings ever!
You're making my heart flutter
out of control right now!
If I were a big and vigorous
man, I would throw caution
to the wind and take this
opportunity to overpower you and
plunge my raging passion into
your soft and ready yaoi hole!
Yeah.
You lost me on that one, sorry.
It's an awful shame,
don't you agree?
No.
But what you're
saying to me is a shame!
Ugh.
Besides, there is no
such thing as a yaoi hole!
No, that isn't true.
Rika told me all about it.
[RIKA]
You don't have a yaoi hole.
[YUKIMURA]
Really?
Right.
Of course she did.
[PHONE]
You've got mail.
It's Rika.
[RIKA] Please come to
the roof right away.
If you're not here in three
minutes, Rika will broadcast
to the whole school the
secret recording she made
of your lovely and
dramatic Boy Love reading.
What recording?
[YUKIMURA]
Big Brother?
Sorry.
I have to go.
But will you take those papers
to the student council room
for me, please?
Of course, I can do that.
Thanks, I owe you one!
Big Brother, wait!
Good luck in battle.
Thanks.
[RIKA] Three minutes,
twenty-six seconds.
Rika will let it slide,
this time.
Oh, whatever, Rika.
I bet you don't even
have a recording of me.
[KODAKA]
--desperate for my boy hole.
My ass is hungry, Teacher,
and wants a bite of your--
You seriously recorded that?
[RIKA] Don't act so
surprised with Rika.
[KODAKA]
Fine.
What do you want from me?
[RIKA] Rika doesn't
necessarily want something.
It's more like
she wants to inflict
a little torture upon you,
what with the lying.
After all, you acted like you
valued the Neighbors Club,
but still ran out
on us like a loser.
[KODAKA]
Look, I'm sorry.
Meek isn't normally your style.
[KODAKA]
If it makes you feel any better,
I know I deserve
anything you say.
So punch me, kick me,
whatever makes you feel better.
Whatever you say, Kodaka.
[KODAKA]
What are those?
[RIKA]
They're a form of artillery.
Rika can control them
via brain waves.
The Nine Lives Breaker.
Rika took the name
from a powerful spell
in Fullmetal Necromancer.
[KODAKA]
What do they do?
[RIKA] It's probably easier
just to show you.
Shatter the very soul
of Rika's enemy!
[pained screaming]
Damn, Rika.
Don't you think
that's a bit much?
[RIKA]
Not really.
Rika's not strong enough
to cause you pain herself.
But that is hardly enough
reason to allow you to escape
the punishment that
you so richly deserve.
Rika is rather angry.
So she is going to
use these to train you.
Next time you'll think
twice before running away!
I did not run away;
I was just really busy.
[RIKA] A sudden love confession
would throw anyone off.
Rika's pissed about
your behavior afterwards.
It's been over a week,
and you have yet to
come back to the club.
And now what,
you're like new best friends
with that horrible girl
who tried to disband us?
What are you talking about?
Aoi's not my best friend!
So you admit
you're friends with her?
On top of that,
you've started flirting with
the student council president!
Seduced by a sexy older woman!
You're just a sick
and twisted gigolo!
You're wrong Rika.
I wasn't seduced by her
sexiness, like, at all.
But Hinata is cool.
And I do like her personality,
she's not crazy as hell!
Rika will never
forgive you for that!
Yeah, okay.
That was out of line.
I apologize.
Your personality is great, too!
Too late for sorry!
Tell Rika the truth, you've
probably already conveniently
yet somehow accidentally
walked in on her naked.
You have, haven't you?
What?
How'd you know about that?
Oh no.
You mean Rika
was actually right?
How can you be so
disgustingly stereotypical?
[KODAKA]
I can't take much more.
Artillery she controls
with her brain waves?
Then, those cat ears
must be the antennae!
Balls, attack!
Damn it.
I can't get close enough.
Rika asked Sena
when she fell for you.
You saved her from
some boys at a pool.
Hold on to that one,
so you'll know you were
a man once upon a time.
It wasn't long before you tried
to get all up in her gutter.
[KODAKA]
Shut up!
And you've just been clearing
flags ever since that day;
I know you stayed
the night at her house!
No, it wasn't like that!
[RIKA]
What the hell?
She ended up being your
friend since you were a kid
and your fiancée?
That's a total troll character!
Then take that up with her!
Not that you care,
but because of that,
Yozora is completely depressed!
Yeah, I already know.
Yozora and I have
an important past,
and she's been using it
for emotional support.
I'd help her if I knew how!
[RIKA]
Important past.
If who you met first
is really that important,
then you might as well suck
on your mom's teats forever.
Emotions aren't
just some experiment
you can control, Rika.
You really don't get it, do you?
But go on.
Keep up the good work
clearing those flags with
one girl after another!
Be that lame anime harem
hero who gets all the girls
because he's just so damn nice!
Yeah, anime harem hero; I wish.
You know what.
I wish I could give
everyone a happy ending.
But life isn't
some romantic anime.
And I can't fix what's wrong
in life stumbling around
being oblivious and
nice all the time!
Believe it or not this isn't
very easy for me, either.
I know that I'm not the hero.
I will most likely
never be the hero.
Surprise, I'm just
as scared as you are!
[RIKA]
So you take it out on Rika?
Real classy!
[KODAKA]
I never said I was classy!
I never said I was anything.
The club is a place
I've never had.
It's like a miracle.
A home where freaks like us
can just be who we are
without feeling like
we had to hold back.
I don't want to screw that up.
But that is exactly what
I was doing, and you know it!
[RIKA] This whole thing is
meaningless if it ends up
making you hold back!
You've pretended to be the
oblivious guy since day one!
And when you couldn't fake
it anymore, you ran away!
What's the point of loving
somewhere so much that you
feel like you have to leave
just so you can protect it?
We never asked you to sacrifice
yourself at the altar of
The Neighbors Club,
so don't be stupid!
You think you can talk?
Fuck you!
Who's playing the
sacrifice card again?
Oh, you pretend to be
Little Miss Class Clown.
Meanwhile, you never stop
working behind the scenes
to make sure
everything is perfect!
You're too damn
good to all of us!
And here you are, taking
the thankless role again!
You're just as guilty
of holding back as I am.
Both of us are doing our best.
What the hell else do you want?
C'mon.
What do you think Rika wants?
What did we start
this dumb club for?
For friends.
I want friends.
All I want are friends!
[KODAKA screaming]
[RIKA]
Rika's sorry, Kodaka.
She lied about controlling those
things with her brain waves.
[KODAKA]
Then what are the ears for?
They're just a toy that uses
brainwaves to make them twitch.
Really?
That's kinda cool.
[KODAKA collapsing, moaning]
You sure are
a tough fighter, Rika.
[RIKA]
Same to you.
The truth is,
Rika can't stand anymore.
She's exhausted.
Yeah, me too.
[RIKA]
Hey, Kodaka?
[KODAKA]
What's up?
[RIKA] If you can't fix
things on your own, please,
ask Rika for help.
Remember, Rika is
literally a genius.
She eats impossible
problems for breakfast.
So hey, Rika?
[RIKA]
Yeah?
Whaddayasay?
You wanna maybe be my friend?
Huh?
What did you say?
[KODAKA]
"What did you say" my ass.
Don't be stupid.
[RIKA] Yeah, well, don't be
stupid yourself, stupid.
I'm already your friend, right?
We all already are your friends.
[KODAKA laughing]
[KODAKA]
It was then I realized,
ten years ago had
happened all over again.
You're wrong.
I'll prove I'm not weak!
[KODAKA] Except this time,
Sora's not here.
Neither is proud little
Taka for that matter.
It's just weak,
pathetic, probably fractured,
Kodaka Hasegawa.
Rika, will you help me, please?
[RIKA]
Sure thing.
[KODAKA] Well, this is one
for the Neighbors Club
History Books.
We made friends.
Hey, Sena.
I wanted to-- Well, I--
[PHONE]
You've got mail.
[YOZORA]
I'm leaving on a journey.
Please don't come
looking for me.
[EVERYONE screaming]
What?
[KODAKA]
Of course.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
Looks like our tragically flawed
youth isn't over just yet.