It's that time
of year again.
People everywhere are
flocking to their local beaches
to try to beat this heat.
It's a sight to see.
The shore's so packed
with umbrellas;
you can hardly see the sand.
We're live at the
Yumigahama Beach
--where it looks like a...
--A swimsuit?
Huh? You okay...?
What's wrong?
Kobato! There you are!
I've been looking
for you everywhere!
-So?
-So.
What games should
we play today?!
None.
We could hit the pool
and shout marco polo?
No!
How cute...! She's
totally rejecting me!
What about you, did you
bring your swimsuit?
I did... Stupid Yozora
told me to, just in case.
-We're here.
-Ha, ha...!
You're so hilarious!
-A horse?!
-The hell?
[Music]
I never would've guessed I'd
encounter the demon Astaroth
in a place like this.
Wait, I thought the
evil gate was destroyed
during the last war
between God and the Devil.
Stop it, you're
creeping me out.
Yozora?
-That's Yozora?!
-Indeed.
What are you doing
dressed up like that...?
You weirdo...
It's creepy.
Don't... Stay back.
Get away from me, freak...!
You're gross.
Dammit...!
What was that for?!
Someone wanna tell
me what's going on?
-Today is swimsuit day!
-It is?
Yeah, the plan was to wear
swimsuits all day at the club.
Why would we do that?
Because it would be a shame
not to wear my swimsuit
after all the
money I spent.
This is all your fault;
you just had to go home!
The pool was too crowded;
it was impossible
to have any fun.
You could barely get in,
much less find
a place to sit.
Are you serious?
Uh... Yeah... I am.
So what's going on...?
Like... Why in the hell are
you wearing that horse mask...
Not to mention the full
bodied zebra swim suit.
It's embarrassing
to show your skin
in front of a bunch
of strangers.
And like you said,
the pool was packed.
With this outfit,
my flesh isn't exposed,
and no one can see my face,
so I can keep my dignity.
If you went to the pool
wearing that ridiculous thing,
everyone would hate you.
They can hate me
all they want,
there's no rule that says
I can't wear a horse mask.
Yeah, maybe not,
but I'm pretty sure there's
a rule against freak shows.
Then they wouldn't
let you in either.
You take that back!
When you walk into
a swimming pool,
everyone immediately
starts throwing up.
Hey, Kodaka.
Rika's wearing a swimsuit
under her coat...
Wanna take a look?
Uh... Not really.
Rika thinks you'll
like it a whole lot!
It's called...
"The Emperors
New Swim Suit!"
That's no suit,
that's going nude!
Why don't you
sneak a peek then?
Knock it off, all right?!
Rika's just
pulling your chain.
Come on...
Tell Rika how she looks.
You look pretty normal.
What...? Normal...?
It might seem that
way on the outside...
But this suit's special...
Once it gets in hot water,
it's completely see thru.
Rika... Stop!
Rika will take him to a private,
secluded hot spring.
He'll think Rika's wearing
a regular swimsuit,
but before his very eyes,
she'll emerge from the
hot water totally naked!
Kodaka will lose control
and give into his carnal desires
rising up from deep within!
Not gonna happen...
I wouldn't go to a
hot spring with you,
not if my life
depended on it.
Why not?
Hey... Big bro, it's you!
Oww. A monster!
There's a monster in here!
No, it's okay...
She's just...
Guess what little girl,
I'm-a gonna eat you!
Oh, please
don't do that...
I'm raw...
I don't taste good raw!
Don't worry I'll throw
you on the grill first.
No, I still won't taste good,
not even then!
Plus, all I've been
eating are vegetables!
Good, cause
I'm a vegetarian!
Oh no!
If I would've known
this was gonna happen,
I never would've
stopped eating steak,
I would have given myself
a nice fat, flabby flavor
-so he wouldn't want me!
-She doesn't eat steak? Weird.
Recently, Maria
changed her diet...
She decided she was
really into normal food.
Do it, horse devil!
Take that girl out...!
Start at the head and
munch your way down
to the toes of that
snobby agent of God!
Okay, this is just
getting ridiculous.
I see... You're a friend of the
blood sucker, aren't you...?!
You and that
stupid, moronic,
poop head of a vampire
can both rot in hell!
It's time for you to die!
I like my little
girls medium rare,
-so after I throw you on the...
-Don't eat me...!
Somebody rescue
me, please!
Okay, Yozora, I think
she's had enough.
Oh, all right.
Oh no... It turned
into Yozora...!
Be gone now you devil!
The mask has secret
dark powers...
If you put it on,
the demon Astro
takes over your body
and possesses you...
Now the power's
taking over my hands.
I can't see anything,
its pitch black in here!
I got some bad news
for you Church Lady;
the power of darkness has now
fully invaded your mind.
But I don't wanna be a
horse monster forever...!
Help me!
If you really want help,
then swear you'll never go
near my brother again!
Never...!
I love Big Brother!
Don't you dare say you
love him, you stupid head!
Ah! It's off...!
You just broke the curse!
That's what you get, turd!
Why you... you... you what...?
Ho bag!
Yozora, I've
got an idea...
Since you don't want your
swimsuit to go to waste,
how 'bout we go
to the beach?
But that place is packed
to the brim with people.
We could always go to my
family's private beach instead.
-Wait... Private beach?
-Yeah...
We've got a place
right by the water.
It Figures... Rich girl.
Well... To be
completely honest,
I've only been
there one time,
back when I was
little kid...
Besides, it's so far away
you have to plan
to stay overnight.
Hold on... Does that mean
we'd be able to go out there
and hold a training camp
sometime over the summer?
Oh yeah...
I guess we could...
Actually, that
sounds really fun.
Like an overnight
club field trip!
Plus... This could be
a perfect experience
to prepare all of us
for what life will be like
when we become 'happy people.'
Sounds good...
I'll ask my Daddy then.
So... It's okay
to set it up...?
Does anyone have any
plans they know about?
I'm guessing we're free...
I mean, let's face it,
it's not like
we have any friends.
Way to bring the
whole room down.
But wait... I don't know
what a training camp is?
Huh. We will need
an advisor...
Good point.
It's still piping hot and
it's still very crowded.
If you're planning on
making a trip to the beach
with your
friends or family,
you better get there
early and grab a spot,
-Hey.
-Uh... Hello?
Hi there...
This is Sena Kashiwazaki...
Is Kodaka available?
Relax, Sena...
Don't you know this is
my cell phone number?
Huh?
Oh yeah. Right, I knew that.
So... What's going on?
Uh, are you free today by
any chance? Kobato, too?
Yeah, just have to drop
by the club after lunch.
Great! Then come
to my house!
Why? Do you remember
what you said before...?
About wanting to pay
respects to my father?
Yeah, but this is
kind of outta nowhere.
Well... The thing is,
when I asked him about us
using the summer house,
I mentioned your name...
And now Daddy says he
wants to meet you 'asap.'
-How come?
-I don't know...
Would you mind
coming over?
Uh... Yeah, I'll be there.
Great, I guess all you'll
need are directions then.
Cool, let me
write them down.
The due date's written
down on the card,
He won't be there?
Oh, wow.
All right, here we go.
Um... Hello.
Good day to you both.
Thank you for coming
all this way...
I am President
of the Academy...
But I moonlight
as Sena's Dad, too.
Uh... It's very nice
to meet you, sir...
My name is Kodaka...
This is my younger
sister, Kobato.
Has anyone told you
that you look exactly
like your father...?
This one's lucky enough
to have Airi's lovely face.
Please dine with us...
Come...
This way.
Sir. Wait...
It's extremely rude
to invite someone
into your home
without giving them
your name first.
Right...
I'm Mister... Kashiwazki.
That's my name...
But you can call
me 'heaven stud.'
Wait, 'heaven stud?'
That's really your name?
No, his name's Pegasus.
Pegasus?
How dare you insult
me by calling me that?!
Sorry...
It's... just...
people made fun of me
a lot in high school...
I'm real sensitive.
No... I understand.
My name's Stella,
I'm the official
steward of this house.
Steward?
Please don't stare
at me like that, sir,
it makes me uncomfortable...
I fear you might
get me pregnant.
Is a steward the same
thing as a butler?
At first I thought
Stella was Sena's mother.
Sorry this is
all so new to me.
My wife's currently
vacationing around the world.
I gotta say I'm surprised,
it's not very often
you take the time
to greet our guests
at the door, Daddy.
That's true.
He's been very anxious
about meeting the two of you;
he's hasn't stopped
talking about it all week.
Hey... I have not been
anxious about anything...!
Now bring out the
damn food already!
As you wish, sir.
Wow!
Everybody, dig in.
Thanks for the food...!
-Yay!
-Go ahead...
Eat as much as you like!
Don't forget manners... Okay?
Thanks for the food.
Oh yeah...
Umm... Sir...
Thank you for helping us
get into the academy...
It seems like my Dad asked
you for a pretty big favor.
That's true
it was indeed...
Right when the entrance
season is over,
I hear from him...
That idiot father of yours
called me up outta the blue
and all but demanded,
"You better let my
son and daughter
in that fancy
school of yours."
Well... I'm very
sorry about that.
You two aren't
exactly the same...
Unlike him, you know
what manners are.
That's right...! Here...
It's our way of
saying thank you.
Well, what is it?
A world-famous
spicy sesame oil...
Next time you cook a meal,
add in a little bit of this,
and I promise you
won't regret it.
Thank you?
Trust me, it can make
everything taste better...
It goes good with rice,
pasta, really anything...
Even Kobato likes it
and she hates spicy food.
Do you mind if I open one?
Please, go ahead.
That's good!
You're right...!
This stuff is awesome!
Glad you like it.
Me too! I want some!
Well... Then your big sister
will feed you some more!
Well...
Maybe you're more like
him than I thought;
he was always
the master of
finding unusual
spices for his food.
Thank you... I guess
that's what happens
when you move around from
town to town your whole life...
He's out traveling right
now, as a matter of fact.
After all these years,
the man's not changed...
I'm not surprised.
That must've been
hard on you kids.
Unbelievable...
Devoting his wasted life
to digging up ruins,
and then dragging his own
kids into it, the scum.
He's not scum!
Uh... I'm sorry.
Sir... I don't think it's
fair to call my dad scum.
He's just a
hardworking guy.
Oh, you don't have
to tell me, I know.
Stay here...?
Tonight?
It's not an
imposition at all.
Uh... It's not that,
it's just...
Actually, on weekends,
the buses stop at eight...
So it looks like you don't
have much choice in the matter.
Huh?
If you absolutely have
to get home tonight...
I suppose it's possible
I could give you a ride.
But honestly,
it would be a pain.
Right... We don't
want that, do we?
Come on, just stay over.
But... We didn't bring
pajamas or anything.
That's no excuse,
you can wear mine...!
That's what your
old man used to do
whenever he spent the night.
And Kobato, I've got
an old pair of p.j.'s
that would fit
you perfectly.
Umm... Well...
But where will we...?
We have a guest room
you can sleep in.
I don't know.
Thank you for
the kind offer.
She's cute when
she's sleeping, too.
Don't touch her,
you'll wake her up.
My Daddy likes you...
I'm surprised, that doesn't
happen often at all...
It's been a
long time since
I've seen him in a
good mood like this.
I'd hate to see
his bad mood.
He really loved you.
Uh... Bro...
What happened,
where are we?
You're at my
house, silly...
How about you and me take
a bath together before bed?
A bath...
But why?
Uh... Hey... Kobato...
It wouldn't hurt
you to skip a night.
Come on, let's get
you cleaned up!
President.
Care for a nightcap?
I appreciate it, sir, but
the thing is, I'm a minor.
Relax, will ya?
It's regular grape juice...
Have a drink with me.
I don't know about this.
Mine...? It's
the real deal...
Sure you don't
wanna trade?
No, it's like I said,
I'm a minor...
I'm just kidding.
Back in the day
when we were students,
your Dad and I drank this
stuff by the barrel.
That's cool, I guess I'm
standing in for my Dad.
Way to take it down, son!
Hey, it's just
grape juice, right?
Uh... Are you gonna be okay?
Huh...?! I'm fine... Why?
He chugged it
down like water!
Back in our shtuden daysh
yo dad and I used to
love to dwink dis...
A... Lot!
Back in our shtuden
daish we used to drink!
Back in the day...
We used to sdrink...
It was good...
Ah ha!
You all right...?!
Please sir, you've
really gotta wake up!
Uh... How do you feel?
Wonder if I should
let Stella know?
What's wrong?
Big bro!
What happened to you?
Uh. Kobato, wait...!
Don't run away!
Oww.
What in the world are you doing
out here, spying on me...?!
You stupid, perverted,
disgusting, molesting,
peeping Tom freak boy!
Hey that's no way to talk
to one of your father's
guests, is it?!
My life is over!
Why'd she go outside?
Beats the heck outta me.
Well, well, well...
Looks like
Kodaka's a pervert.
No way, this isn't what
it looks like, I promise!
Don't worry, I know.
Come... Let's get
you to bed...
While you still
have a chance.
Wait... The President
got drunk on wine
and fell asleep in there.
Once he's out,
there's no way
he'll get out of
bed till morning,
especially when he's
been drinking heavily.
I'll put her to bed in
the servant's quarters,
she should be just fine there
for the rest of the night...
I'm very sorry but
there's no more room...
You and the master
of the house
are going to have to
share a bed tonight.
Um... Can I sleep in
the servant room?
I sleep naked and don't
wanna get pregnant.
Fine then, I'll just
go sleep with him.
You and my Dad used to
drink wine together
back in the old days...
Cool.
There's no question...
The President
thinks of my Dad
as being one of the closest
friends he's ever had.
That makes sense...
I guess that's why Dad
felt comfortable
leaving me and Kobato behind
to go off on his own.
It does make you think...
I wonder if I'll ever make a
friend like that someday.
Well, we're off...
Thank you so much for letting
us both stay the night.
Of course.
Kobato.
Uh... Okay...
Um... Thank you...
The food was good.
You're welcome here
anytime you like.
Thanks, that's very kind.
Next time, how about we take
another hot bath together?
No!
Nooooooooo!
She's freaked...
What did you do to her?
Don't look at me,
I didn't do a thing!
That aside... Kodaka?
What's up?
Uh... Well I...
I wanted to talk to you about
what happened last night.
What do you mean?
It's all a blur...
Your Dad made me chug wine
with him after dinner...
I can't remember a
single thing that happened.
Did I do something?
Uh... Well...
No.
Nothing at all!
Hey, Kobato...!
Wait for me!
Sometimes it's best to
say you don't remember,
even if it is a lie.
-Oh, Kodaka?
-Yeah?
Hey... Let go of me!
Do this much...
Take care of my daughter.
Yes, of course.
Pegasus.
You twerp!
I gotta go...
Thank you so much.
Stella, what are you...?!
All right!
[Music]
When I woke up
in the morning,
an old man's sleeping face
was only centimeters
away from me!
Hayato! Oh no, you say my
Dad's name in your sleep!
Where did you come from?
Why are you in my bed?
What in the name of everything
holy is going on here?!
I'm Kodaka,
Hayato's son,
and this is supposed
to be my bed!
You're the one
who got wasted and...
So you're saying
nothing happened?!
Sorry, you're not my type!
Next. No one sleeps at camp!
Really? If you're telling
me little white lies,
I swear, I will
never forgive you.
That's actually kinda cute.