&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHY SHOULD WEHAVE TO SHARE
THESE HEALING CRYSTALS WITH YOU?
YOUR PET LIZARDS HASHEALING
POWERS, YOU KNOW.
&gt;&gt; [ SQUEALS ]
&gt;&gt; BUT YOU NEVER FIGHT ON THE
FRONT LINES, SO WHO ARE YOU TO
TALK?!
YOU DON'T NEED TO USE ANY
CRYSTALS!
&gt;&gt; OF COURSE I DO.
YOU'RE THE POPULAR ONE AROUND
HERE, SILICA.
I CAN'T EXPECT THE BOYS TO HELP
ME WHEN INEED IT.
&gt;&gt; [ SQUEALS ANGRILY ]
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
&gt;&gt; FINE. I DON'T CARE.
YOU WANT MY ITEMS, TAKE 'EM, BUT
I'M NEVER GOING TO TEAM UP WITH
YOU AGAIN.
I KNOW THERE'S A TON OF OTHER
PARTIES OUT THERE WHO'D LOVE TO
HAVE ME ON THEIR SIDE.
&gt;&gt; WAIT! DON'T GO! SILICA!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
&gt;&gt; [ PANTING ]
&gt;&gt; [ SHRIEKS ]
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; I'M OUT OF HEALING CRYSTALS!
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SHRIEKS ]
&gt;&gt; PINA!
&gt;&gt; [ CRIES WEAKLY ]
&gt;&gt; PINA! PINA!
PINA.
PINA!
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; [ Crying ] PINA.
DON'T LEAVE ME ALL ALONE HERE.
PINA!
[ SOBBING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S THAT FEATHER?
&gt;&gt; IT'S PINA, MY BEST...FRIEND.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE
BEAST TAMERS, AREN'T YOU?
I'M SORRY.
IF I GOT HERE SOONER, I COULD
HAVE SAVED YOUR FRIEND.
&gt;&gt; NO. IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
I WAS STUPID TO THINK I COULD
MAKE IT THROUGH THE FOREST ON MY
OWN.
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
YOU DID WHAT YOU COULD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT FEATHER...
CHECK AND SEE IF IT HAS AN ITEM
NAME ATTACHED TO IT.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
[ SOBBING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, DON'T CRY.
THAT MEAN'S PINA'S HEART'S STILL
HERE.
THERE'S A CHANCE YOU CAN REVIVE
&gt;&gt; NO WAY. REALLY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM-HMM.
ON THE SOUTH SIDE OF FLOOR 47,
THERE'S A FIELD DUNGEON CALLED
THE HILL OF MEMORIES.
I HEARD SOMEWHERE THAT THE
FLOWER GROWING AT THE TOP CAN
REVIVE FAMILIARS.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
FLOOR 47, HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'D OFFER TO GO GET
IT FOR YOU.
ALL YOU'D HAVE TO DO IS PAY FOR
THE TRIP.
THE THING IS, THE FLOWER WON'T
BLOOM UNLESS THE FAMILIAR'S
MASTER'S THERE.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR TELLING
ME ABOUT IT.
IF I WORK HARD TO RAISE MY
LEVEL, THEN SOMEDAY I COULD...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SURE, BUT THE TIME
LIMIT'S THREE DAYS TO REVIVE IT.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
NO WAY.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
I'M SO SORRY, PINA.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S OKAY.
YOU HAVE THREE DAYS.
TAKE THIS EQUIPMENT.
IT SHOULD BOOST YOU 5 OR 6
LEVELS, AND IF I TAG ALONG, I'M
SURE EVERYTHING WILL WORK OUT.
&gt;&gt; BUT...WHY WOULD YOU DO ALL
THIS FOR ME?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL TELL YOU, BUT
ONLY IF YOU PROMISE NOT TO
LAUGH, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; I PROMISE I WON'T.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ALL RIGHT.
IT'S BECAUSE YOU LOOK LIKE MY
LITTLE SISTER.
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS LIGHTLY ]
[ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANS ]
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY.
[ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; UM...I KNOW THIS ISN'T ENOUGH
COL TO PAY YOU BACK, BUT --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, IT'S COOL.
BESIDES, IT WORKS WITH WHY I'M
HERE.
WE'LL BE HELPING EACH OTHER OUT.
&gt;&gt; HUH? OKAY, THEN.
MY NAME'S SILICA.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MY NAME'S KIRITO.
I GUESS WE'LL BE WORKING
TOGETHER FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; HEY, LOOK! IT'S SILICA!
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; IT TOOK YOU A LONG TIME TO
GET BACK.
WE WERE GETTING WORRIED.
&gt;&gt; UM...
&gt;&gt; YOU WANT TO TEAM UP WITH US?
WE'LL TAKE YOU WHEREVER YOU WANT
TO GO!
&gt;&gt; THAT'S REALLY NICE OF YOU TO
OFFER, BUT...
WELL, I'VE SORT OF ALREADY
AGREED TO BE IN A PARTY WITH
HIM, SO...
&gt;&gt; Both: [ GRUMBLE ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ LAUGHS AWKWARDLY ]
&gt;&gt; 'KAY, LATER. BYE.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO PUT YOU ON THE
SPOT LIKE THAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD
FANS.
YOU MUST BE POPULAR.
&gt;&gt; NO.
THEY DON'T TAKE ME SERIOUSLY.
THEY WANT ME TO BE THEIR MASCOT.
&gt;&gt; [ CALLS HAPPILY ]
&gt;&gt; MAYBE THEY'RE RIGHT.
THEY CALL ME DRAGON TAMER, AND I
GUESS...IT WENT TO MY HEAD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T WORRY ABOUT
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE'LL MAKE IT IN
TIME, PROMISE.
&gt;&gt; OKAY!
DO YOU LIVE AROUND HERE, KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M ON FLOOR 50.
IT'S KIND OF FAR, SO I WAS
THINKING OF GETTING A ROOM
TONIGHT.
&gt;&gt; IF YOU STAY, I'LL TAKE YOU
OUT FOR SOME CHEESECAKE!
IT'S REALLY GOOD HERE!
&gt;&gt; WELL, IF IT ISN'T SILICA.
WOW, YOU MADE IT OUT OF THE
FOREST ALIVE.
GOOD FOR YOU, GIRL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: Something wrong?
&gt;&gt; OH, NO. NOTHING.
&gt;&gt; HANG ON.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR LITTLE
FRIEND THE LIZARD?
DID IT RUN AWAY?
&gt;&gt; PINA DIED SAVING ME.
BUT...I'M GONNA GET PINA BACK!
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
I GUESS YOU'LL BE HEADING FOR
THE HILL OF MEMORIES, THEN.
I WONDER IF YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
CLEAR IT AT YOUR LEVEL.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OF COURSE SHE WILL.
IT'S NOT THAT DIFFICULT A LEVEL.
&gt;&gt; OH, GOD, THIS GIRL'S SEDUCED
ANOTHERPLAYER.
NO, IT'S NOT DIFFICULT, BUT YOU
DON'T LOOK THATSTRONG.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME ON.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; WHY DOES SHE HAVE TO BE SO
MEAN?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL...IS
SWORD ART ONLINE YOUR FIRST MMO?
&gt;&gt; UH-HUH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: A LOT OF PEOPLE'S
PERSONALITIES CHANGE WHEN THEY
PLAY GAMES ONLINE, AND SOME
ACTUALLY LIKE PLAYING THE GAME
AS THE BAD GUY.
YOU SEE HOW OUR CURSORS ARE
GREEN?
WELL, IF YOU COMMIT A CRIME
AGAINST ANOTHER PLAYER, YOUR
CURSOR'S GONNA TURN ORANGE.
THEN THEY BECOME WHAT'S CALLED A
RED PLAYER -- THE WORST, ALSO
KNOWN AS PLAYER-KILLERS.
THEY'RE ALL ABOUT MURDER.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
THEY KILL OTHER PLAYERS?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IN A NORMAL GAME,
THEY ROLE-PLAY AS THE BAD GUY,
HAVE SOME LAUGHS, AND IT'S COOL.
BUT...SWORD ART ONLINE ISN'T
NORMAL.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S DEFINITELY NOT
A GAME.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M SORRY.
&gt;&gt; WELL, I THINK YOU'RE GOOD,
SO...
I MEAN, YOU SAVED ME, AFTER ALL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
LOOKS LIKE YOUCHEERED MEUP
INSTEAD.
THANK YOU, SILICA.
&gt;&gt; AAAH!
WOW, WHERE THE HECK IS OUR
CHEESECAKE ALREADY?!
EXCUSE ME!
OUR DESSERT HASN'T SHOWN UP YET!
[ SIGHS ]
[ GROANS ]
I WONDER IF HE'D LAUGH IF I TOLD
HIM I WANTED TO TALK SOME MORE.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SILICA?
YOU STILL AWAKE?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
KIRITO?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I FORGOT TO TELL YOU
SOME STUFF ABOUT FLOOR 47, BUT
IT CAN WAIT TILL TOMORROW.
&gt;&gt; NO, NOW'S FINE!
ACTUALLY, I WAS JUST THINKING I
SHOULD ASK YOU ABOUT --
THAT WAS SO CLOSE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, WHAT'S UP?
SOMETHING WRONG?
&gt;&gt; NO! NOTHING!
WHAT'S THAT THING DO, KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S A MIRAGE
SPHERE.
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
IT'S PRETTY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THIS IS THE TOWN
AREA OF FLOOR 47, AND THAT'S
THE HILL OF MEMORIES.
I WAS THINKING IF WE TAKE THIS
ROUTE, WE CAN --
HMM?
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S WRO--
&gt;&gt; Kirito: Shh!
WHO'S THERE?!
[ RUNNING FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING ]
&gt;&gt; UM...WHO WAS IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AN EAVESDROPPER.
&gt;&gt; BUT THEY CAN'T.
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T HEAR THROUGH A
DOOR UNLESS YOU KNOCK FIRST.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT IF YOUR
LISTENING SKILL IS HIGH ENOUGH,
YOU CAN.
IT TAKES PRACTICE.
NOT THATMANY PLAYERS HAVE IT.
&gt;&gt; WHY WOULD THEY WANT TO LISTEN
TO US?
[ BIRDS SINGING ]
&gt;&gt; WOW!
THIS PLACE IS LIKE A DREAM!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW.
THE WHOLE FLOOR IS COVERED IN
FLOWERS.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT THE
FLOWER GARDEN.
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ Thinking ]COUPLES!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SILICA?
&gt;&gt; WHAT?! NOTHING!
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; OH, NOTHING! NOTHING AT ALL!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME ON.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
WHAT'S THAT FOR?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF ANYTHING BAD
HAPPENS WHILE WE'RE IN HERE, I'M
GONNA TELL YOU TO WARP OUT,
OKAY?
WHEN I DO, USE THIS CRYSTAL.
YOU CAN JUMP TO ANY TOWN WITH
&gt;&gt; BUT...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO "BUTS." USE IT.
&gt;&gt; I UNDERSTAND.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LET'S GET GOING.
IF WE TAKE THIS PATH, IT'LL LEAD
US RIGHT TO
THE HILL OF MEMORIES.
&gt;&gt; UM, KIRITO?
[ SCREAMS ]
AAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CALM DOWN!
THAT THING'S NOT THATSTRONG!
&gt;&gt; HELP, KIRITO! SAVE ME!
BUT DON'T LOOK!
SAVE ME, BUT DON'T LOOK!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT'LL BE...
DIFFICULT.
&gt;&gt; DARN YOU! PUT ME DOWN! NOW!
&gt;&gt; [ GURGLING ]
[ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU SEE ANYTHING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOT REALLY.
&gt;&gt; I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND ME
ASKING, BUT WHAT'S YOUR SISTER
LIKE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY DO YOU WANT TO
KNOW?
&gt;&gt; WELL, YOU SAID I LOOK LIKE
HER.
I KNOW IT'S NOT POLITE TO ASK
ABOUT YOUR REAL LIFE, BUT...
WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I CALL HER MY LITTLE
SISTER, BUT SHE'S REALLY MY
COUSIN.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE WERE RAISED LIKE
BROTHER AND SISTER SINCE WE WERE
BABIES, SO I DOUBT SHE EVEN
KNOWS.
BUT I KNOW, AND I GUESS THAT'S
THE REASON I AVOIDED HER.
OUR GRANDFATHER'S REALLY STRICT.
WHEN I WAS 8, HE MADE US TAKE
CLASSES AT THE LOCAL KENDO DOJO,
BUT AFTER A COUPLE YEARS, I
STOPPED GOING.
GRANDPA BEAT THE HELL OUT OF ME
FOR THAT.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S AWFUL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ANYWAY...
THEN MY SISTER STOOD UP FOR ME
AND TOLD HIM TO STOP.
SHE SAID SHE'D TRAIN HARD FOR
BOTH OF US.
AND SHE DID. SHE TRAINED HARD.
SHE EVEN MADE IT TO THE
NATIONALS.
&gt;&gt; SHE DID? HOW AWESOME!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
I'VE ALWAYS FELT GUILTY FOR
PUTTING HER THROUGH THAT.
I WOULDN'T DOUBT IT IF SHE HATES
GOD KNOWS SHE COULD HAVE BEEN
DOING SOMETHING ELSE.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY I WANTED TO
HELP YOU.
IN A WEIRD WAY, IT MAKES ME FEEL
LIKE I'M PAYING HER BACK.
THERE IT IS.
&gt;&gt; IF YOU DON'T MIND ME SAYING,
YOU'RE WRONG.
I DON'T THINK SHE HATES YOU AT
ALL.
SHE WOULDN'T WORK THAT HARD FOR
YOU IF SHE DIDN'T LIKE YOU,
PROMISE!
AND I BET SHE EVEN LOVES KENDO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE YOU GO AGAIN,
MAKING MEFEEL BETTER.
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAN, I HOPE SO.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, THEN!
I'M GONNA DO MYBEST, TOO!
AAAAH!
KIRITO!
[ GIGGLES ]
[ GASPS ]
IS THAT REVIVING FLOWER AROUND
HERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. OVER THERE.
GO AHEAD. PICK IT UP.
&gt;&gt; YOU SURE IT'LL BRING PINA
BACK TO LIFE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
&gt;&gt; I'M SO GLAD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE'S A BUNCH OF
STRONG MONSTERS LURKING AROUND
HERE.
LET'S REVIVE IT WHEN WE GET BACK
TO TOWN.
I'M SURE PINA WOULD WANT IT THAT
WAY.
&gt;&gt; OKAY!
[ GIGGLES ]
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOEVER'S HIDING OUT
THERE, COME OUT -- NOW!
&gt;&gt; ROSALIA?
&gt;&gt; IF YOU SAW THROUGH MY HIDING
SKILL SO EASY, YOUR DETECTION
SKILL MUST BE REALLY HIGH,
SWORDSMAN.
OOH!
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU WERE
SUCCESSFUL GETTING YOUR HANDS ON
THE PNEUMA FLOWER!
CONGRATULATIONS.
NOW, HAND IT OVER BEFORE YOU GET
HURT.
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO ONE'S HANDING
ANYTHING OVER, ROSALIA...
NOT TO YOU OR THE ORANGE GUILD,
OR SHOULD I SAY TITAN'S HAND.
YOU'RE THEIR LEADER, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; NICE.
&gt;&gt; BUT ROSALIA'S CURSOR IS
GREEN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S AN EASY TRICK.
THE GREEN MEMBERS FIND THEIR
VICTIMS, THEN THEY LURE THEM
STRAIGHT TO THE ORANGE PLAYERS
FOR THE AMBUSH.
THAT WAS ONE OF YOUR PALS LAST
NIGHT EAVESDROPPING ON US,
WASN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; THEN THE REASON YOU WERE IN
THAT PARTY WITH ME AND THE
OTHERS WAS TO --
&gt;&gt; HOW PERCEPTIVE.
I WAS OBSERVING THEIR STRENGTH
AND WATCHING THEM EARN ALL THAT
BEAUTIFUL MONEY.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU WERE WHO I WAS EXCITED
ABOUT, AND I WAS SO SAD WHEN YOU
LEFT THE PARTY, BUT THEN YOU
TOLD ME YOU WERE GETTING A RARE
ITEM.
WHAT I WANT TO KNOW IS IF YOU
KNEW ABOUT US, WHY DID YOU BRING
HER HERE?
ARE YOU DUMB, OR DOES SHE HAVE
YOU WRAPPED AROUND HER FINGER?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOPE.
YOU'RE WRONG BOTH TIMES.
SEE, I'VE BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER
FOR YOU,ROSALIA.
>> WHAT AREYOU TALKING ABOUT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: REMEMBER 10 DAYS
AGO?
YOU ATTACKED A GUILD CALLED THE
SILVER FLAGS?
THE LEADER SURVIVED, FOUR
DIDN'T.
&gt;&gt; OH, THE LOSERS WITH NO MONEY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEIR LEADER WENT
BACK AND FORTH FROM THE WARP
POINT TO THE FRONT LINES,
MORNING TILL NIGHT, AND WITH
TEARS IN HIS EYES, HE BEGGED
EVERYONE HE MET TO AVENGE HIS
DEAD FRIENDS.
BUT HE DIDN'T WANT YOU KILLED.
NO, HE WANTED YOU TO GO TO
PRISON.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW HE
FELT?
&gt;&gt; CAN'T SAY I DO.
ONLY IDIOTS TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY.
SO WHAT IF WE KILL SOMEONE HERE?
THERE'S NO PROOF DYING HERE
MEANS YOU'RE DEAD I.R.L.
ANYWAY, IT'S TIME YOU STARTED
WORRYING ABOUT YOURSELVES.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO, THERE'S TOO MANY OF
THEM.
WE SHOULD GET OUT OF HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, IT'S OKAY.
YOU'LL BE SAFE IF YOU STAY HERE.
KEEP THE CRYSTAL HANDY TILL I
SAY SO.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, BUT...
KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; KIRITO?!
DRESSED IN BLACK, ONE-HANDED,
NO SHIELD.
HOLY CRAP!
IT'S THE BLACK SWORDSMAN!
ROSALIA, THAT GUY...
HE'S THE BEATER WHO PLAYS SOLO
ON THE FRONT LINES!
HE'S WITH THE ASSAULT TEAM!
&gt;&gt; NO WAY! HE IS?!
&gt;&gt; WHY WOULD SOMEONE FROM THE
ASSAULT TEAM BE ALL THE WAY DOWN
HERE?
GO ON! TAKE HIM OUT!
AND TAKE EVERYTHING HE OWNS!
&gt;&gt; DIE!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; I'VE GOT TO SAVE HIM.
HE WON'T LAST!
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ ALL PANTING ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT THE HELL, YOU IDIOTS?
KILL HIM ALREADY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: 400 IN 10 SECONDS,
GIVE OR TAKE -- THAT'S ABOUT THE
TOTAL DAMAGE THE SEVEN OF YOU
CAN INFLICT ON ME.
I'M LEVEL 78.
I GOT 14,500 H.P.
MY BATTLE-HEALING SKILL
AUTO-REGENERATES 600 POINTS
EVERY 10 SECONDS.
WE COULD STAND HERE ALL DAY, AND
YOU WOULDN'T GET ANYWHERE.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WANT TO BET?
IF YOUR NUMBERS ARE HIGH ENOUGH,
YOU'RE INVINCIBLE.
MMOs THAT USE LEVELING SYSTEMS
ARE UNFAIR THAT WAY.
MY CLIENT SPENT HIS ENTIRE
FORTUNE ON THIS WARP CRYSTAL,
AND HE'LL GET HIS MONEY'S WORTH.
IT'S BEEN SET TO THE COORDINATES
OF THE PRISON.
AND I'M SENDING ALL OF YOU
BASTARDS THERE!
&gt;&gt; WELL, I'M GREEN, AND IF YOU
HURT ME, YOU'LL GO ORANGE --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M A SOLO PLAYER,
GOT IT?
I DON'T CARE IF I HAVE TO PLAY
AS ORANGE FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M REALLY SORRY,
SILICA.
THIS WHOLE TIME, I WAS USING YOU
AS BAIT TO CATCH 'EM.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE SCARED IF I
TOLD YOU THE TRUTH ABOUT ME.
&gt;&gt; I COULD NEVER BE SCARED OF
YOU 'CAUSE YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON.
UM...DO YOU REALLY HAVE TO GO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
I'VE BEEN AWAY FROM THE FRONT
LINES FOR FIVE DAYS.
I NEED TO GET BACK.
&gt;&gt; I...I THINK IT'S COOL YOU'RE
WITH THE ASSAULT TEAM!
I COULD TRY FOR 100 YEARS AND
NEVER MAKE IT.
UM...I...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU KNOW, LEVELS ARE
JUST NUMBERS.
AND A PERSON'S STRENGTH IN THIS
WORLD IS JUST AN ILLUSION.
SURE, IT'S COOL AND ALL, BUT
THERE ARE MORE IMPORTANT THINGS
THAN THAT.
WE SHOULD MEET UP IN THE REAL
WORLD.
THAT WOULD BE COOL 'CAUSE I LIKE
HAVING YOU AS A FRIEND.
&gt;&gt; OKAY. WE WILL. I PROMISE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, READY TO
REVIVE PINA?
&gt;&gt; YEAH!
PINA, WHEN YOU GET BACK, I'LL
HAVE LOTS OF STUFF TO TELL YOU
ABOUT...
ABOUT THE AMAZING ADVENTURE I
HAD...
...AND ABOUT THIS ONE DAY WHEN
I GOT TO HAVE MY VERY OWN BIG
BROTHER.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]