[ CHAIR CREAKING ]
[ CHIPMUNK CHITTERING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
ASUNA!
ASUNA!!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
OH, ASUNA.
I'VE TURNED INTO THE BIGGEST
CRYBABY.
HAVEN'T I?
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; ME AND HIM, WE LOOK NOTHING
ALIKE.
[ GRUNTS ]
I'M OFF TO PRACTICE!
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ PANTING ]
[ SIGHS ]
HU--
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GOOD MORNING, SUGU.
&gt;&gt; U-UH, G-G-GOOD MORNING.
UH -- OH, EH, EH, UH!
GOD, SERIOUSLY?
INSTEAD OF LURKING, YOU SHOULD
HAVE SAID SOMETHING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, WELL, YOU WERE
PRACTICING, AND I DIDN'T WANT TO
BOTHER YOU.
>> I WASN'T REALLY PRACTICING.
I GUESS IT'S JUST HABIT, IS ALL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. HUH.
AT LEAST YOU'VE BEEN KEEPING IT
IT'S LIGHT.
&gt;&gt; WHAT?!
IT'S NOT LIGHT.
IT'S TIMBER BAMBOO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. YEAH, RIGHT.
I MEANT, LIKE...
IT'S LIGHTER THAN I THOUGHT.
IT'S NOT AS HEAVY AS WHAT I'M
USED TO.
&gt;&gt; OH.
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GULPING ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT THE HECK'S HE COMPARING
IT TO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AHH.
HEY, YOU THINK MAYBE WE COULD
GIVE IT A GO?
&gt;&gt; WHAT, YOU MEAN A MATCH?
LIKE, SERIOUSLY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUP.
&gt;&gt; A REAL MATCH WITH PADS AND
STUFF?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM...
YEAH, ON SECOND THOUGHT, NO
CONTACT.
I MEAN, I'D FEEL LIKE CRAP IF I
ENDED UP HURTING YOU.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS LIGHTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I STILL GOT TO DIG
OUT GRANDPA'S OLD GEAR.
HOW 'BOUT WE SPAR IN THE DOJO?
&gt;&gt; WHOA!
YOU SOUND PRETTY DARN CONFIDENT
FOR SOMEONE WHO'S BEEN ASLEEP
FOR TWO YEARS.
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, I WAS A
QUARTERFINALIST IN THE
MIDDLE-SCHOOL NATIONALS.
SERIOUSLY, THOUGH, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE FEELING UP TO THIS?
YOU MIGHT WANT TO TAKE IT EASY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES LIGHTLY ]
I'VE BEEN DOING REHAB IN THE GYM
EVERY DAY, SO I THINK I'M GONNA
BE GOOD TO GO.
&gt;&gt; EH...HM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHAT KIND OF STANCE IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO BE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT
THIS IS MY OWN STYLE.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
READY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
>>HIS HEAD'S WIDE OPEN.
THAT'LL BE MY FIRST STRIKE.
HUH?
IT'S AN ODD STANCE, BUT HE
LOOKS COMPOSED.
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
>>OKAY, THEN.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ YELLS ]
[ STRAINING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ YELLS ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, MY GOD!
A-A-ARE YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANS LIGHTLY ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
OKAY, OKAY. YOU WIN.
YOU SURE ARE STRONG, SUGU.
YOU'D MOP THE FLOOR WITH
HEATHCLIFF.
&gt;&gt; MAYBE YOU SHOULD SIT DOWN OR
SOMETHING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M GOOD.
THANKS FOR THE MATCH.
&gt;&gt; UH...HUH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
[ GASPS ]
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
&gt;&gt; D-DID I HIT YOU TOO HARD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, I'M OKAY!
JUST YEARS OF HABIT.
LET'S SEE.
MY FOOTWORK WAS OKAY, BUT THE
ATTACK SUCKED.
I GUESS I CAN'T USE THE SWORD
SKILLS I ACQUIRED, UNLESS I GOT
THE SYSTEM HELPING.
&gt;&gt; I HAVE TO SAY, I'M REALLY
SURPRISED.
I MEAN, HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
PRACTICING BEHIND MY BACK?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, YOU KNOW...
IT ISKINDA FUN, AFTER ALL.
BUT YOU NEVER KNOW -- MAYBE I'LL
TAKE IT UP AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?!
OH, SERIOUSLY?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, SURE.
YOU WANT TO BE MY TEACHER?
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU KIDDING? OF COURSE!
WE'LL TRAIN TOGETHER, LIKE WE
USED T--
[ GIGGLES ]
>> Kirito: AFTERI BUILD UP SOME
MORE MUSCLE, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; I'VE BEEN PRACTICING, TOO.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
NOPE. I'LL KEEP IT A SECRET.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT IS SO NOT COOL.
&gt;&gt; YOU GOING ANYWHERE TODAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS...THE HOSPITAL.
&gt;&gt; OH, YOU ARE?
THAT'S NICE.
HER NAME'S ASUNA, RIGHT?
YOU...VISIT HER A LOT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
AS MUCH AS I CAN.
IT'S THE ONLY THING I CAN DO FOR
HER.
ANYWAY, SUGU, IT'S MYTURN TO
MAKE BREAKFAST TODAY.
IT'LL BE READY BY THE TIME YOU
FINISH YOUR SHOWER.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
>> Kirito: IT'S BEEN TWO MONTHS
SINCE I BEAT HEATHCLIFF.
TWO MONTHS SINCE I BEAT THE
DEATH GAME.
WHEN I WOKE UP, I TALKED TO
SOMEONE FROM THE MINISTRY OF
INTERNAL AFFAIRS.
I TOLD THEM EVERYTHING I KNEW
ABOUT S.A.O., AND IN EXCHANGE,
THEY TOLD ME WHERE ASUNA WAS.
I FOUND OUT SHE WAS NEARBY, IN
SAITAMA.
ASUNA'S FAMILY ADMITTED HER TO
TO KOROZAWA GENERAL HOSPITAL.
I ALSO FOUND OUT THAT BESIDES
HER, THERE'S ABOUT 300 OTHER
PLAYERS WHO HAVEN'T WOKEN UP
YET.
AKIHIKO KAYABA'S STILL MISSING.
AND PEOPLE THINK HE'S KEEPING
THE PLAYERS IN THEIR COMAS AS
PART OF HIS PLAN.
S.A.O. ISN'T OVER.
NOT BY A LONG SHOT.
ASUNA.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
&gt;&gt; KAZUTO.
SORRY -- I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE
HERE.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HELLO, MR. YUKI.
I HOPE IT'S OKAY I'M HERE.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE.
YOU CAN VISIT WHENEVER YOU LIKE.
I KNOW IT MAKES HER HAPPY.
[ PAPER CRINKLES ]
&gt;&gt; SIR.
&gt;&gt; OH.
I DON'T THINK THE TWO OF YOU
HAVE EVER MET.
THIS IS SUGOU.
HE'S OUR COMPANY'S DIRECTOR OF
R&amp;D.
&gt;&gt; I'M NOBUYUKI SUGOU.
IT'S A PLEASURE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M KAZUTO KIRIGAYA.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
YOU'RE THE KIRITO?
YOU'RE A HERO.
IT'S AN HONOR!
&gt;&gt; OH. I-I'M SORRY.
I KNOW WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
TALK ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED INSIDE
THE S.A.O. SERVER.
BUT HE'S MY PARTNER'S SON, SO
IT'S FINE.
BESIDES, I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT OF
HIM AS PART OF MY FAMILY.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
UH, ACTUALLY, SIR...
SPEAKING OF FAMILY...
IF I MAY, I'D LIKE TO MAKE IT
OFFICIAL AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
>> THIS IS SUDDEN.
ARE YOU SURE THIS IS REALLY WHAT
YOU WANT?
I MEAN, YOU'RE STILL YOUNG.
YOU HAVE YOUR WHOLE LIFE AHEAD
OF YOU.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU FOR YOUR CONCERN,
BUT MY HEART'S SET ON IT.
IT SOUNDS STRANGE, BUT EVEN
THOUGH SHE'S LIKE THIS, SHE'S
STILL BEAUTIFUL.
I'D LIKE TO SEE HER IN THAT
WEDDING DRESS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE A POINT.
THE SOONER WE PREPARE OURSELVES
FOR THE INEVITABLE, THE BETTER.
SORRY TO CUT THE CONVERSATION
SHORT.
I HAVE A MEETING TO GET TO.
WE CAN TALK MORE ABOUT THIS
LATER.
KAZUTO, TAKE CARE.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
&gt;&gt; I HEARD YOU AND ASUNA WERE
LOVERS IN THE GAME.
IS THAT TRUE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
&gt;&gt; THAT IS UNFORTUNATE.
IT'S GOING TO MAKE FOR ONE
COMPLICATED RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN
YOU AND I.
[ SNIFFS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; IN CASE YOU'RE CURIOUS, HER
FATHER AND I WERE DISCUSSING HER
MARRIAGE -- TO ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO WAY.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE A POINT.
IT'S TRUE.
WE CAN'T LEGALLY MARRY.
BUT IF THE YUKI FAMILY ADOPTS
ME, IT'LL BE AS IF WE ARE --
ON PAPER, THAT IS.
JUST LIKE WE'RE MARRIED.
THE TRUTH IS, SHE'S ALWAYS HATED
ME -- EVER SINCE WE WERE KIDS.
NEITHER MY PARENTS NOR HERS KNOW
THAT.
IF I PROPOSED AND SHE COULD
SPEAK, I'M PRETTY SURE HER
ANSWER WOULD BE "NO."
[ CHUCKLES ]
FOR ME, THIS SITUATION IS...
VERY FAVORABLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: STOP IT!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHO DO YOU THINK YOU
ARE?
YOU CAN'T TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
ASUNA LIKE THIS.
&gt;&gt; "TAKE ADVANTAGE"?
OH, PLEASE.
IF ANYTHING, I HAVE A RIGHT TO
HER.
PERHAPS I SHOULD EXPLAIN WHY.
ANY IDEA WHAT HAPPENED TO ARGUS?
THEY'RE THE COMPANY THAT
DEVELOPED S.A.O.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I HEARD THEY CLOSED
IT DOWN.
&gt;&gt; VERY GOOD.
THE LAWSUITS AND DAMAGES THEY
HAD TO PAY TOOK THEIR TOLL.
THE COMPANY WAS FORCED INTO
BANKRUPTCY.
BUT THE MAINTENANCE OF THE
S.A.O. SERVERS WAS GIVEN TO
ANOTHER COMPANY -- AN
ELECTRONICS MANUFACTURER, WHERE
ASUNA'S FATHER, SHOUZOU YUKI,
IS THE C.E.O. -- RCT PROGRESS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; AND I WORK FOR THE COMPANY'S
FULL-DIVE TECHNOLOGY R&amp;D
DIVISION.
IN OTHER WORDS -- AND WITHOUT
GETTING INTO SPECIFICS -- YOU
COULD SAY I'M THE ONE KEEPING
ASUNA ALIVE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; NOW, I ASK YOU -- IS IT WRONG
FOR ME TO EXPECT A LITTLE
COMPENSATION FOR MY TROUBLE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND OF
PROMISES YOU MADE TO EACH OTHER
IN THE GAME, AND I DON'T REALLY
CARE.
BUT I DON'T EVER WANT TO SEE YOU
HERE AGAIN.
UNDERSTOOD?
AND FROM NOW ON, STAY AWAY FROM
THE YUKI FAMILY.
WE'RE HAVING THE CEREMONY HERE
ON JANUARY 26th -- A WEEK FROM
NOW.
SAVE THE DATE.
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE NOT WELCOME
HERE ANYMORE, YOU SHOULD COME TO
THE WEDDING.
NO NEED TO THANK ME.
WELL, MR. HERO, YOU'VE GOT THE
ROOM ALL TO YOURSELF NOW.
SAY "GOODBYE" AND GET OUT.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
&gt;&gt; KAZUTO!
THE BATHROOM'S ALL YOURS!
GEEZ. WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?
AND TURN ON THE HEAT.
IT'S FREEZING IN HERE!
[ BEEP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SORRY.
I JUST...WANT TO BE LEFT ALONE.
&gt;&gt; HEY, HOW COME YOU DIDN'T TURN
THE HEATER ON?
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, IT'S NOTHING.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, BUT...
YOU'RE FREEZING.
YOU'RE GONNA CATCH A COLD.
I COULD RUN YOU A HOT BATH, IF
YOU WANT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SOBBING SOFTLY ]
I'M SO HOPELESS AND WEAK.
[ SNIFFLES ]
I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO SEE THIS.
I SWORE, NO MATTER WHAT, YOU'D
NEVER SEE ME BEING SUCH A
CRYBABY.
[ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; IS IT ASUNA?
IS SHE OKAY?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO HER?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SHE'S LEAVING...
SOMEWHERE FAR AWAY.
AND I'LL NEVER -- I'M NEVER
GONNA SEE HER AGAIN.
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; HEY.
HANG IN THERE, OKAY?
IF YOU REALLY LOVE SOMEONE THAT
MUCH, EVEN WHEN THINGS LOOK
HOPELESS, YOU CAN'T GIVE UP.
I KNOW I CAN'T.
AND I WON'T LIE TO MYSELF
ANYMORE.
&gt;&gt; GOSH.
I REMEMBER IT LIKE IT WAS
YESTERDAY.
KAZUTO STOOD THERE LOOKING AT
ME, AND THEN HE TOLD ME HE
WANTED TO KNOW WHO HIS REAL
PARENTS WERE.
I WAS SO SHOCKED, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
HE WAS ONLY 10, BUT HERE'S THE
THING -- SOMEHOW, HE LOGGED ON
TO THE CITIZEN'S REGISTRATION
NETWORK AND FOUND THE FILE!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
THAT FIGURES.
SOUNDS JUST LIKE SOMETHING HE'D
&gt;&gt; I WAS SO STUNNED, I COULDN'T
THINK OF A WAY TO DENY IT.
SO WHAT DO I DO INSTEAD?
I TELL HIM HOW MY BIG SISTER
AND HER HUSBAND ARE HIS REAL
PARENTS.
WOW!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
&gt;&gt; MOM?
I WAS WONDERING...
&gt;&gt; ABOUT WHAT?
&gt;&gt; I GUESS ABOUT THE WAY HE'S
BEEN SINCE MIDDLE SCHOOL.
HE'D GO INTO HIS ROOM AND PLAY
GAMES ONLINE FOR HOURS.
YOU THINK IT'S 'CAUSE HE FOUND
OUT ABOUT HIS REAL PARENTS?
&gt;&gt; NO, NOT AT ALL.
HE WAS ALWAYS INTO COMPUTERS AND
TECHNOLOGY.
BY THE TIME HE WAS 6, HE'D
ALREADY BUILT HIS OWN COMPUTER
OUT OF SPARE PARTS.
IF ANYTHING, HE'S LIKE THAT
'CAUSE HE'S A HUGE COMPUTER
NERD, LIKE ME.
OR SO HE THINKS.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; WELL, I'M HEADING HOME AND
GET DINNER READY.
DON'T STAY TOO LONG, OKAY,
SUGUHA?
&gt;&gt; DON'T WORRY. I WON'T.
&gt;&gt; HAPPY BIRTHDAY, KIDDO.
[ FOOTSTEPS DEPART ]
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
HE'S MY COUSIN, NOT MY BIG
BROTHER.
I STILL HAVE A HARD TIME
BELIEVING IT.
MY BIG BROTHER.
BUT...
IN THE END, YOUR HEART...
BELONGS TOHER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME ON.
WAKE UP, SUGU.
IT'S MORNING.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I SAID YOU GOT TO
WAKE UP NOW.
NOT GONNA HAVE TIME TO PRACTICE
IF YOU DON'T WAKE UP.
&gt;&gt; UH...WHA...?
OH. HEY.
MORNING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: RISE AND SHINE.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
[ YAWNS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HIYA, SLEEPY.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
UM, I --
OH, MY GOD!
[ SQUEALS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
AS WEIRD AS EVER.
&gt;&gt; JUST HANG IN THERE, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SHE'S RIGHT.
YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.
[ BEEP, WARBLE ]
WHAT THE HELL?!
[ BREATHES SHAKILY ]
[ GASPS ]
ASUNA.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]