[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LURE IT TO THE
VILLAGE.
THAT'S HOW WE GET THE BOSS.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: W-WAIT -- YOU CAN'T
BE SERIOUS.
IF WE DO, THE BOSS'LL GO AFTER
THE VILLAGERS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YES, THAT'S THE IDEA.
AND WHILE THE BOSS IS BUSY
KILLING NPCs, WE CAN ATTACK IT
AND KILL IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT THEY'RE NOT JUST
OBJECTS.
NPCs ARE DIFFERENT THAN ROCKS
AND TREES!
L-LOOK, THEY'RE --
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU THINK THEY'RE
ALIVE?
REALLY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
>> Asuna: IN THIS GAME, THEY ARE
JUST OBJECTS, AND UNLIKE US, IF
THEY ARE KILLED, THEY CAN ALWAYS
RESPAWN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SORRY, BUT I'M NOT
COOL WITH THAT PLAN.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M RUNNING THIS
OPERATION, OKAY?
IN CASE YOU FORGOT, I'M STILL
SECOND-IN-COMMAND OF THE
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH.
YOU'LL OBEY MY ORDERS, LIKE IT
OR NOT.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: HEY.
WHAT'S WITH YOU GUYS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Agil: YOU AND THE
SECOND-IN-COMMAND -- YOU'RE
ALWAYS GETTING INTO IT, AND NOT
IN A GOOD WAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I GUESS WE JUST DON'T
CLICK, AGIL.
YOU CAN BECOME POWERFUL HERE ON
YOUR OWN, BUT IF THE DAY COMES
WHEN SOMEONE YOU TRUST INVITES
YOU TO JOIN A GUILD, DON'T TURN
IT DOWN.
WELL, SHE TOOK MY ADVICE, BUT
WHO KNEW SHE'D JOIN THE TOP
GUILD AND BE A FLOOR-CLEARING
BAD-ASS?
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM?
[ SIGHS ]
OH, HEY. WHAT'S UP?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: EVERYONE IN THE
ASSAULT TEAM'S WORKING THEIR
BUTTS OFF TO CLEAR THE DUNGEON,
AND WHERE DO I FIND YOU?
OUT HERE, TAKING A NAP.
EVEN IF YOU'RE A SOLO PLAYER,
YOU SHOULD TAKE THIS MORE SE--
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BET YOU DIDN'T KNOW
THIS IS AINCRAD'S NICEST SEASON.
TODAY'S WEATHER IS AT ITS
OPTIMAL SETTING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'D BE A WASTE TO
HAVE TO GO TO WORK ON A DAY LIKE
THIS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHATEVER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
DO YOU EVEN UNDERSTAND WHAT'S
GOING ON?
EVERY DAY HERE IS ANOTHER ONE
LOST IN THE REAL WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, BUT RIGHT NOW
WE'RE NOT IN THE REAL WORLD, ARE
WE'RE ALIVE IN AINCRAD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SEE?
DOESN'T THAT BREEZE FEEL GOOD?
AND THE SUN?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH, COME ON.
THE WEATHER IS ALWAYS THE SAME
HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ YAWNS ]
IF YOU LAID DOWN ON THE GRASS
FOR A LITTLE BIT, YOU'D
UNDERSTAND.
[ SNORING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMM.
MM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
[ YAWNS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SNORING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
DAMN, WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
&gt;&gt; TAKING A NAP IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE DAY.
&gt;&gt; SOME PEOPLE SURE GOT IT EASY.
&gt;&gt; [ Chuckling ] COUPLE OF LAZY
LOSERS, MAN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE
FELL ASLEEP.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
[ SNEEZES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHING ]
HUH?
[ GASPS ]
WHAT? UH, UH...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GOOD MORNING.
YOU SLEPT LIKE A ROCK.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
[ GROANS ]
YOU GET ONE MEAL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: ONE MEAL -- ALL YOU
CAN EAT, MY TREAT.
THEN WE'LL BE EVEN. DEAL?
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ]
&gt;&gt; THAT'S ASUNA FROM THE
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, THEY CALL HER THE
LIGHTNING FLASH.
&gt;&gt; WHO IS THE SHADY-LOOKING GUY
DRESSED IN BLACK?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WELL, ANYWAY...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THANK YOU FOR TODAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: FOR KEEPING AN EYE ON
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. SURE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THE TOWNS ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE SAFE ZONES, AND UNLESS
YOU'VE AGREED TO A DUEL, A
PLAYER CAN'T ATTACK OR KILL YOU.
BUT WHEN YOU'RE ASLEEP, YOU'RE
VULNERABLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
NOW WE'VE GOT PLAYER-KILLERS WHO
CAN CHEAT THE DUEL SYSTEM.
DUELS ARE NORMALLY SUPPOSED TO
BE TESTS OF STRENGTH, NOT A
FIGHT TO THE DEATH.
BUT EVEN IF YOU DUEL IN A SAFE
ZONE, YOUR H.P. IS STILL GONNA
GO DOWN BASED ON THE DAMAGE YOU
TAKE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: ALL A SLEEP P.K.er HAS
TO DO IS MANIPULATE A SLEEPING
PLAYER'S FINGER TO CLICK THE
"OKAY" BUTTON -- THE DUEL BEGINS
LIKE NORMAL.
BUT THE SLEEP P.K.er IS DOING
ALL OF THE ATTACKING.
GOD KNOWS HOW MANY TIMES IT'S
HAPPENED.
SO, ANYWAY, THANK YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, SURE. ANYTIME.
WELL, YOU'D DO THE SAME FOR ME.
[ WOMAN SCREAMS ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ ROPE STRETCHING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING, GROANING ]
[ CROWD GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HURRY! PULL IT OUT!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'LL CUT HIM DOWN.
YOU CATCH HIM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GOT IT.
[ GRUNTS ]
HELP'S ON THE WAY!
DAMN IT.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANING ]
[ CROWD GASPS ]
[ WOMAN SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Thinking ] THE ONLY
WAY HE COULD HAVE DIED IN A SAFE
ZONE IS IF HE WAS BEATEN IN A
DUEL.
THAT MEANS...
EVERYONE, LOOK FOR THE PLAYER
WITH THE "WINNER" ICON!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THERE'S NO ONE HERE!
THE ROOM'S EMPTY!
[ WHIRRING, BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
SO, ANY IDEA HOW THIS COULD HAVE
HAPPENED?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WELL, THERE IS ALWAYS
THE OBVIOUS -- THERE WAS A DUEL,
AND THE OTHER GUY IMPALED THE
VICTIM WITH THAT SPEAR.
THEN HE PUT A NOOSE AROUND HIS
NECK AND PUSHED HIM OUT THE
WINDOW.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY THAT'S ABOUT
RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, BUT I COULDN'T
SEE THE "WINNER" ICON ON ANYONE.
>> Asuna: IT HADTO BE A DUEL --
IT'S A SAFE ZONE, AND A PLAYER
DIED.
A DUEL IS THE ONLY THING IT
COULD HAVE BEEN.
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
OR MAYBE NOT.
EITHER WAY, WE CAN'T IGNORE
THIS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AS IT IS, A PLAYER
TAKES HUGE RISKS GOING OUTSIDE A
SAFE ZONE, BUT IF SOMEONE'S
FOUND A WAY TO P.K. INSIDE,NO
ONE'S GOING TO BE SAFE IN THE
TOWNS, EITHER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I GUESS WE WON'T BE
GOING BACK TO THE FRONT LINES
ANYTIME SOON.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LISTEN, YOU'RE GOING
TO WORK WITH ME UNTIL WE SOLVE
THIS THING.
UNTIL WE DO, THERE WON'T BE ANY
TIME FOR NAPPING, OKAY?
>> Kirito: OKAY, BUT YOU'RETHE
ONE WHO WAS NAPPING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OW!
[ WINGS FLUTTER ]
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
LISTEN UP -- DID ANYONE SEE WHAT
HAPPENED BEFORE THAT PLAYER
DIED?
IF SOMEONE DID, PLEASE SPEAK UP.
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SORRY.
I CAN IMAGINE HOW FRIGHTENED YOU
ARE.
COULD YOU TELL US YOUR NAME?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPING ]
SURE.
MY NAME IS YORUKO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
WAS THAT YOU?
I MEAN, WERE YOU THE ONE WHO
SCREAMED?
&gt;&gt; UH, UH-HUH. I-I KNEW HIM.
HIS NAME WAS KAINS, AND THE TWO
OF US USED TO BELONG TO THE SAME
GUILD.
ANYWAY, WE CAME HERE TOGETHER
TODAY.
WE WERE GOING TO HAVE DINNER
SOMEWHERE IN TOWN.
BUT WE GOT SEPARATED IN THE
PLAZA.
I LOOKED AROUND FOR HIM, AND
THEN I SAW HIM HANGING FROM THAT
BALCONY, AND...
[ SOBBING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WAS THERE ANYONE ELSE
UP THERE?
&gt;&gt; FOR A SECOND THERE -- I'M NOT
SURE -- BUT I THINK I DID SEE
SOMEONE STANDING BEHIND KAINS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AND THIS PERSON, HAD
YOU SEEN THEM BEFORE?
&gt;&gt; [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
MNH-MNH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UM, I KNOW THIS IS
HARD FOR YOU, BUT THINK BACK AND
TRY TO REMEMBER -- COULD THERE
BE SOMEONE, ANYONE,WITH THE
REASON TO KILL HIM?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPING ]
MNH-MNH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU FOR WALKING ME
BACK.
SORRY IF IT'S OUT OF YOUR WAY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO WORRIES.
BUT WE'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU
AGAIN TOMORROW IF YOU'RE FEELING
UP TO IT.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO, WHAT DO WE DO?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SIMPLE -- WE FOLLOW
THE ONLY SOLID CLUE WE HAVE.
IF WE CAN FIND OUT WHERE THAT
SPEAR CAME FROM, IT MIGHT LEAD
US STRAIGHT TO THE KILLER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE'LL NEED TO FIND
SOMEONE WITH AN APPRAISAL SKILL.
I MEAN, IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS YOU
DON'T HAVE ONE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO, I DON'T, AND
NEITHER DO YOU.
OH, AND BY THE WAY, TRY NOT TO
BE SO RUDE WHEN YOU'RE SPEAKING
TO ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
UH, OKAY.
SHOULD I CALL YOU MISS NEXT
TIME?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SECOND-IN-COMMAND?
LIGHTNING FLASH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
OH, NEVER MIND.
CALL ME ASUNA.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY. SURE.
BACK TO THE APPRAISAL SKILL,
THOUGH -- DO YOU KNOW ANYONE WHO
HAS IT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMM.
I'VE GOT A FRIEND WHO DOES.
SHE'S A WEAPONS MERCHANT.
BUT SHE'S REALLY BUSY THESE
DAYS, SO I DON'T THINK SHE'LL
HAVE TIME TO HELP US.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO WORRIES -- I
HAPPEN TO KNOW AN ITEM MERCHANT
WHO MIGHT BE ABLE TO HELP US
OUT.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; THANKS, MY MAN.
COME BACK ANYTIME.
&gt;&gt; YEAH. WHATEVER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
STILL RUNNING ALL THE SUCKERS
DOWN WITH THOSE HARD DEALS OF
YOURS.
&gt;&gt; Agil: NO WAY -- KIRITO!
BUY CHEAP AND SELL CHEAP --
THAT'S MY MOTTO.
I'M A BUSINESSMAN.
YOU KNOW THAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT "SELLING CHEAP"
PART'S A LIE, THOUGH.
&gt;&gt; Agil: DON'T GO SLANDERING MY
GOOD NAME, BROTHER.
[ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; Agil: WHAT THE HELL HAS
GOTTEN INTO YOU?!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE A SOLO
PLAYER, MAN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HANGING
AROUND WITH ASUNA?!
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS HATED EACH
OTHER'S GUTS, STRAIGHT UP!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLING ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: WHAT'S THE DEAL?!
HIS H.P. DROPPED TO ZERO IN A
SAFE ZONE?
YOU SURE IT WASN'T A DUEL?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, NO ONE SAW A
"WINNER" ICON.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AND WE CAN ALSO RULE
OUT THE MURDER BEING A SLEEP
P.K.
HE WAS WALKING WITH YORUKO
BEFORE IT HAPPENED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AND, BESIDES, HIS
DEATH WAS TOO ELABORATE TO BE
SOME RANDOM DUEL.
THE P.K.er WHO DID THIS HAD IT
PLANNED OUT.
WE'RE PRETTY SURE OF THAT.
AND THEN THERE'S THIS.
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: HMM.
[ BEEPING ]
A PLAYER MADE THIS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: REALLY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHO WAS IT?
CAN YOU TELL?
&gt;&gt; Agil: "GRIMLOCK."
NEVER HEARD THAT NAME BEFORE.
IT'S NOT ONE OF THE TOP
BLACKSMITHS.
THAT'S FOR DAMN SURE.
FAR AS I CAN TELL, THERE IS
NOTHING SPECIAL ABOUT THIS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, BUT IT'S
SOMETHING TO GO ON, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM-HMM.
IS THERE, LIKE, AN ITEM NAME
LISTED?
&gt;&gt; Agil: YOU'LL LOVE IT --
"GUILTY THORN."
THERE'S A NAME FOR YOU.
IT KIND OF FITS, THOUGH.
DON'T YOU THINK?
[ BEEP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
SERIOUSLY? GUILTY THORN?
[ BEEPING ]
HERE GOES.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
WAIT! STOP!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S THE MATTER?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?!
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?!
THAT THING'S ALREADY KILLED ONE
PERSON!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW.
BUT WE NEED TO FIND OUT WHAT
THIS THING'S CAPABLE OF, DON'T
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WOULD YOU STOP BEING
SO RECKLESS?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AGIL.
WOULD YOU PLEASE HOLD ONTO THIS
FOR US?
&gt;&gt; Agil: UH...YEAH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM.
[ BELL TOLLING ]
SO, UH, YORUKO, WE, UH -- WE
WERE WONDERING IF YOU HAD EVER
HEARD THE NAME GRIMLOCK.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
YES. I HAVE.
ACTUALLY, UNTIL A FEW MONTHS
AGO, HE WAS IN THE GUILD WITH ME
AND KAINS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM.
LISTEN, WE TOOK THE SPEAR THAT
IMPALED KAINS TO AN APPRAISER.
WE HAD HIM GO OVER IT PRETTY
CAREFULLY, AND WE FOUND OUT
GRIMLOCK MADE IT.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CAN YOU THINK OF ANY
REASON WHY HE DID?
&gt;&gt; YES. I CAN.
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU
EVERYTHING YESTERDAY.
IT'S JUST...I COULDN'T.
IT'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN TRYING
VERY HARD TO FORGET.
BUT NOW I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I SHOULD TELL YOU ABOUT HOW MY
GUILD WAS DESTROYED.
WHEN WE FORMED IT,
"GOLDEN APPLE" WAS THE NAME WE
CHOSE.
SIX MONTHS AGO, WE KILLED A
RARE MONSTER.
IT DROPPED A POWERFUL RING THAT
RAISED A PLAYER'S AGILITY BY
SOME OF US WANTED TO KEEP IT
FOR THE GUILD.
OTHERS WANTED TO SELL IT AND
SPLIT THE EARNINGS.
WE COULDN'T AGREE, AND IN THE
END, WE PUT IT TO A VOTE.
IT WAS FIVE TO THREE IN FAVOR
OF SELLING IT.
OUR LEADER, GRISELDA, TOOK IT
TO A LARGE TOWN ON THE FRONT
LINES.
SHE WAS GOING TO SELL IT TO A
BROKER AND WAS STAYING
OVERNIGHT.
WE WAITED AND WAITED, BUT SHE
NEVER CAME BACK.
IT WASN'T TILL LATER WE LEARNED
OUR WORST FEARS HAD COME TRUE --
GRISELDA WAS DEAD.
TO THIS DAY, I STILL DON'T KNOW
HOW SHE DIED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO ONE'S GONNA LEAVE
A SAFE ZONE WITH A RARE ITEM
LIKE THAT -- TOO RISKY.
YOU THINK SOMEONE COULD'VE
PULLED A SLEEP P.K. ON HER?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NOT IF IT WAS SIX
MONTHS AGO -- THAT METHOD'S
STILL SORT OF NEW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT SHE WASN'T A RANDOM VICTIM,
EITHER.
NO, THE KILLER WAS AFTER THE
RING.
IT HAS TO BE SOMEONE WHO KNEW
SHE HAD IT, WHICH MEANS...
&gt;&gt; THE KILLER IS ONE OF THE
SEVEN OTHERS IN OUR GUILD.
YES.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE HAVE OUR SUSPECTS.
NOW WE JUST HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHO DIDN'TWANT TO SELL THE
RING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I DOUBT THE KILLER
WAITED TILL AFTER GRISELDA SOLD
THE RING.
SHE WAS KILLED BEFORE SHE SOLD
THAT'S MY GUESS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: PROBABLY.
TELL US WHAT YOU KNOW ABOUT
GRIMLOCK.
&gt;&gt; WELL, I GUESS, FOR STARTERS,
HE WAS GRISELDA'S HUSBAND -- OH,
BUT NOT IN REAL LIFE, JUST IN
THE GAME.
GRISELDA WAS A POWERFUL
SWORDSWOMAN.
SHE WAS BEAUTIFUL AND SMART.
GRIMLOCK WAS KIND, AND I CAN'T
REMEMBER A DAY WHEN HE WASN'T
SMILING.
THEY MADE A GREAT COUPLE AND
GOT ALONG AS HUSBAND AND WIFE.
IF GRIMLOCK IS REALLY THE ONE
WHO MURDERED KAINS YESTERDAY,
THEN HE'S PROBABLY GOING AFTER
THE THREE GUILD MEMBERS WHO
VOTED AGAINST SELLING THE RING.
KAINS WAS ONE OF THE THREE WHO
WANTED TO KEEP THE RING FOR THE
GUILD.
I WAS THE OTHER ONE.
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN WHO'S THE THIRD
PERSON?
&gt;&gt; THE OTHER'S A TANK NAMED
SCHMIDT, AND HE, THE LAST I
HEARD, IS ON THE FRONT LINES NOW
WITH THE HOLY DRAGON ALLIANCE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SCHMIDT, HUH?
I'VE HEARD THAT NAME BEFORE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HE'S LEADER OF THE
DEFENSE UNIT OF THE
HOLY DRAGON ALLIANCE.
HE'S AN EXCEPTIONAL LANCER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, YEAH. HIM.
&gt;&gt; WAIT -- DO YOU REALLY KNOW
SCHMIDT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, I'VE RUN INTO
HIM A COUPLE TIMES WHILE
CLEARING BOSSES, SO...
&gt;&gt; I NEED TO SEE HIM RIGHT AWAY.
COULD YOU PLEASE TAKE ME TO HIM?
IF HE IS ON THE FRONT LINES, HE
PROBABLY HASN'T HEARD ABOUT THE
MURDER.
HE NEEDS TO KNOW BEFORE WHAT
HAPPENED TO KAINS HAPPENS TO
HIM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE'LL HELP YOU GET IN
TOUCH WITH SCHMIDT.
I KNOW SOMEONE IN THE
HOLY DRAGON ALLIANCE.
HE'LL HELP US OUT.
WE'LL VISIT THEIR H.Q.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
BUT FIRST WE SHOULD MAKE SURE
SHE GETS BACK TO THE INN.
YORUKO, YOU HAVE TO STAY THERE,
OKAY?
SERIOUSLY, DON'T GO ANYWHERE
UNTIL WE GET BACK.
&gt;&gt; ALL RIGHT.
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY, SO, HOW DO YOU
THINK A MURDER LIKE THIS
HAPPENED IN A SAFE ZONE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I CAN SEE THREE WAYS
IT COULD'VE.
RIGHT OFF THE BAT, IT'S POSSIBLE
IT WAS A FAIR DUEL.
OR MAYBE SOMEONE TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF A BUG THAT COMBINES A BUNCH
OF DIFFERENT KILL METHODS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT
HAPPENING.
AND THE THIRD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: USED SOMETHING TO
BYPASS THE PROTECTION OF A SAFE
ZONE -- SOME KIND OF SKILL, OR
MAYBE AN ITEM.
NO, ON SECOND THOUGHT, THAT
THIRD IDEA IS IMPOSSIBLE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BECAUSE IT'S UNFAIR.
I KIND OF HATE TO ADMIT IT, BUT
IT'S TRUE -- THE RULES OF SAO
ARE ESSENTIALLY FAIR FOR EVERY
PLAYER IN THE GAME, SO THERE IS
NO WAY THE GAME WOULD ALLOW
MURDERS IN SAFE ZONES.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I SEE.
&gt;&gt; SO THAT'S WHAT KILLED KAINS.
AND YOU'RE SURE ABOUT THE SPEAR?
WAS IT REALLY GRIMLOCK'S?
&gt;&gt; THERE IS NO DOUBT.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
BUT THEN WHY WOULD HE WAIT SIX
MONTHS TO KILL HIM?!
UNLESS -- WAIT -- COULD HE HAVE
STOLEN THE RING?!
DO YOU THINK IT'S POSSIBLE HE
KILLED GRISELDA AFTER ALL?!
[ GRUNTS ]
DOES GRIMLOCK WANT TO KILL THE
THREE OF US BECAUSE WE DIDN'T
WANT TO SELL THE DAMN RING?!
IS THAT WHY HE'S AFTER YOU AND
ME NOW?!
&gt;&gt; MAYBE GRIMLOCK MADE THE SPEAR
FOR SOMEONE ELSE FROM OUR GUILD,
AND MAYBE THEY'RETHE ONES WHO
KILLED KAINS.
OR MAYBE...
GRISELDA HAS COME BACK FROM THE
DEAD TO GET HER REVENGE.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; A PLAYER CAN'T KILL ANOTHER
PLAYER INSIDE A SAFE ZONE, BUT
SOMETHING ELSE, LIKE A GHOST,
COULD.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] UH...
&gt;&gt; Both: OH.
&gt;&gt; I COULDN'T SLEEP AT ALL LAST
NIGHT, SO I STAYED UP THINKING.
[ OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS ]
IT WAS EVERYONE'S FAULT!
EVERYONE IN THE GUILD IS GUILTY!
HER BLOOD IS ON ALL OUR HANDS!
OUR FATE WAS SEALED WHEN THAT
RING DROPPED!
WE SHOULDN'T HAVE VOTED!
WE SHOULD HAVE DONE WHATEVER
GRISELDA TOLD US TO DO!
[ BOTH GASP ]
GRIMLOCK WAS THE ONLY ONE -- THE
ONLY MEMBER OF THE GUILD WHO
SAID WE SHOULD LEAVE THE
DECISION TO GRISELDA.
YOU SEE?
HE'S THE ONLY ONE OF US WHO CAN
AVENGE GRISELDA.
HE'S THE ONLY MEMBER OF OUR
GUILD WHO HAS THE RIGHT TO
AVENGE HER.
&gt;&gt; YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING.
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING!
WHY NOW?
AFTER ALL THIS TIME, WHY KILL US
NOW?
YOU CAN'T BE OKAY WITH THIS,
YORUKO!
HOW CAN YOU ACCEPT BEING KILLED
OVER SOME STUPID VENDETTA?!
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ THUNK ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
YORUKO!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]