&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
IT'S AMAZING.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
I KNOW. ISN'T IT?
WELCOME TO ARUN.
IT'S THE CENTER OF ALfheim.
IT'S ALSO THE BIGGEST CITY IN
THIS WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
WE FINALLY GOT HERE.
&gt;&gt; HOW EXCITING!
I'VE NEVER BEEN TO A CITY THIS
BIG BEFORE!
&gt;&gt; ME, NEITHER.
THE ORE LIGHT'S SO BEAUTIFUL,
LIKE A BUNCH OF TWINKLING STARS.
[ GONG CRASHES ]
[ ALL GASP ]
&gt;&gt; ATTENTION, PLAYERS.
THE SERVER WILL BE DOWN TODAY,
JANUARY THE 22nd, FROM 4:00 A.M.
TO 3:00 P.M. FOR SCHEDULED
MAINTENANCE.
WE ASK THAT ALL PLAYERS PLEASE
LOG OUT NO LATER THAN 10 MINUTES
BEFORE SHUTDOWN.
REPEAT...
&gt;&gt; [ YAWNS ]
I GUESS THAT DOES IT FOR US FOR
TODAY.
LET'S GO FIND AN INN AND LOG
OUT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SURE.
&gt;&gt; UH...UH...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, I HOPE WE CAN
FIND SOMEPLACE GOOD -- NOTHING
TOO PRICY, THOUGH.
I SORT OF BLEW THREW ALL MY CASH
TODAY.
&gt;&gt; AND WHY IS THAT?
OH, RIGHT -- YOU WERE SHOWING
OFF AND YOU GAVE ALL YOUR MONEY
TO SAKUYA.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SAVED A LITTLE
FOR THE INN, BIG SPENDER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; YOUR DAD'S FINANCIALLY
CHALLENGED.
DO YOU KNOW IF THERE'S A CHEAP
INN ANYWHERE?
&gt;&gt; HMM?
UM...THERE'S ONE THERE, AND FROM
WHAT I CAN TELL, IT'S
SUPERCHEAP!
&gt;&gt; GREAT. SUPERCHEAP. YAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME ON. LET'S GO.
&gt;&gt; HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
[ WIND BLOWING ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AN OPENING.
[ GASPS ]
[ WATER RUNNING ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
&gt;&gt; HEY, SUGU. GOOD MORNING.
&gt;&gt; MORNING, KAZUTO.
[ YAWNS ]
&gt;&gt; SOMEONE LOOKS SLEEPY TODAY.
WHEN DID YOU GET TO BED LAST
NIGHT?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW.
AROUND 4:00, I THINK.
&gt;&gt; WHOA.
A KID LIKE YOU SHOULDN'T BE UP
THAT LATE.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
&gt;&gt; OH, UH, TOOLING AROUND
ONLINE.
&gt;&gt; JUST DON'T GO TOO OVERBOARD,
OKAY?
RIGHT. LIKE I'M ONE TO TALK.
HEY, SUGUHA, TURN AROUND FOR A
SEC.
&gt;&gt; WHY?
&gt;&gt; GO ON. TURN AROUND.
&gt;&gt; OKAY.
[ GASPS ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ BIRDS CHITTERING ]
>> Asuna: HOW FAR DOES THIS
HALLWAY GO?
NO WAY.
IT'S A MAP.
WHERE IS IT?
THERE'S GOT TO BE A CONSOLE
WHERE I CAN LOG OUT.
[ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
EXPERIMENT HANGAR?
&gt;&gt; [ WHINES ]
TO MAKE UP FOR THAT WATER GAG
YOU PULLED, YOU OWE ME ONE
GREEN TEA RASPBERRY PARFAIT.
YOU COOL WITH THAT?
&gt;&gt; ALL RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; THEN WE'RE EVEN.
WE COULD GO GET THEM TODAY IF
YOU'RE NOT TOO BUSY.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
I CAN'T TODAY.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING IN THE
AFTERNOON, AND I WAS ALSO
PLANNING ON GOING TO THE
HOSPITAL.
&gt;&gt; OH, RIGHT.
HEY, I WAS WONDERING -- IS IT
OKAY IF I GO WITH YOU TO THE
HOSPITAL?
&gt;&gt; HUH?
SURE. WHY NOT?
I'M SURE IT'LL MAKE ASUNA HAPPY.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
COME ON. LET'S EAT.
I'M STARVING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
[ BEEPING ]
IS THAT A...
&gt;&gt; DID YOU KNOW THAT BY
EXPANDING THE BRAIN'S CONTROL
REGIONS, ONE COULD INFLUENCE A
PERSON'S THOUGHTS, EMOTIONS, AND
MEMORIES?
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
IT'S SUFFERING!
[ GASPS ]
THEY'RE ALL...PLAYERS.
[ BEEPING ]
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS HORRIBLE.
[ BEEPING CONTINUES ]
HE WON'T GET AWAY WITH THIS --
NOT IF I CAN DO ANYTHING ABOUT
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'LL BE OKAY.
I'M GONNA SAVE YOU.
[ WHOOSH ]
&gt;&gt; TIME TO SEE WHAT EVERYONE'S
UP TO.
&gt;&gt; OOH. THIS GUY'S DREAMING
ABOUT SPICA AGAIN.
HIS B-13 AND B-14 FIELDS ARE WAY
OFF THE SCALE.
HE'S REALLY EXCITED.
&gt;&gt; IT'S ONLY THE THIRD
EXPERIMENT.
MAYBE IT'S A COINCIDENCE.
&gt;&gt; NO, IT'S DEFINITELY THE
INDUCED EMOTION CIRCUIT.
HE'S OVER THE THRESHOLD NOW
BECAUSE OF THE FREQUENCY AT
WHICH THE IMAGERY'S OCCURRING.
&gt;&gt; HMM. THEN WE HAVE TO KEEP
MONITORING HIM.
I'LL PUT HIM ON THE LIST.
&gt;&gt; HEY, I WAS WONDERING --
WHAT'S HAPPENING WITH SCHOOL?
&gt;&gt; WHAT ABOUT IT?
&gt;&gt; IT'S JUST THAT YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO START HIGH SCHOOL
LAST YEAR, AND IT'D SUCK IF YOU
GOT TOO FAR BEHIND.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
THEY SAID SOMETHING ABOUT ME
HAVING TO GO TO SCHOOL IN THE
CITY.
IT'S KIND OF A TEMPORARY THING
THEY SET UP IN AN OLD BUILDING.
MIDDLE-SCHOOLERS,
HIGH-SCHOOLERS -- EVERYONE'S
FROM S.A.O.
&gt;&gt; NOW DEPARTING.
&gt;&gt; YOU CAN GET IN WITHOUT TAKING
THE TEST, AND ONCE YOU GRADUATE,
YOU CAN TAKE THE COLLEGE
ENTRANCE EXAMS.
&gt;&gt; REALLY? HUH.
IF YOU ASK ME, THAT'S A PRETTY
GOOD DEAL.
BUT IT SUCKS THEY'RE CRAMMING
YOU TOGETHER LIKE THAT.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
I GET WHY THEY'RE DOING IT.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT, WE WERE
ALL TRAPPED INSIDE THAT DEATH
GAME FOR MORE THAN TWO YEARS, SO
NO ONE KNOWS WHAT THAT
EXPERIENCE DID TO OUR MINDS.
THIS IS HOW THEY KEEP AN EYE ON
&gt;&gt; SERIOUSLY?
&gt;&gt; IF I WANTED TO GET INTO A
NORMAL HIGH SCHOOL NOW, IT'D BE
WAY TOO HARD.
I'D HAVE TO SPEND A WHOLE YEAR
IN CRAM SCHOOL, BUT THEN I'D
BASICALLY BE STARTING OVER FROM
SCRATCH.
I COULD ALWAYS JUST TAKE THE
EXAMS NOW AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS,
BUT I DOUBT I'D PASS.
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU'D TOTALLY PASS!
YOU'RE SMART, AND YOU'VE GOT
GOOD GRADES.
&gt;&gt; MY GRADES USED TO BE GOOD.
I HAVEN'T STUDIED FOR TWO YEARS,
REMEMBER?
&gt;&gt; I'VE GOT A GREAT IDEA!
I CAN BE YOUR TUTOR!
&gt;&gt; OH, SWEET.
THEN YOU CAN HELP ME WITH MATH
AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Asuna: THERE IT IS...
...THE SYSTEM CONSOLE.
THEY DIDN'T SEE ME. GOOD.
PLEASE WORK.
[ BEEPING ]
[ GASPING ]
[ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
THIS IS IT.
[ BEEPS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; WOW!
THAT'S A BIG HOSPITAL!
&gt;&gt; THE INSIDE'S AMAZING, TOO --
LIKE A HOTEL.
[ ELEVATOR BELL DINGS ]
&gt;&gt; "ASUNA YUKI."
SHE USED HER REAL-LIFE NAME FOR
HER AVATAR.
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING A LOT OF
PEOPLE DO.
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU KNOW
ASUNA'S THE ONLY PERSON I EVER
MET WHO PLAYED UNDER HER REAL
NAME.
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU.
THIS IS ASUNA,
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH,
SECOND IN COMMAND.
THEY CALL HER "LIGHTNING FLASH."
I COULD NEVER MATCH HER SPEED IN
BATTLE OR HER ACCURACY WITH THE
SWORD.
ASUNA, THIS IS MY SISTER,
SUGUHA.
&gt;&gt; UH...HELLO, ASUNA.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTING ]
AAAH! OHH! UGH! OHH!
&gt;&gt; WHO ARE YOU?
YOU WANT TO TELL US WHAT YOU'RE
DOING HERE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
HEY, LET ME GO OF ME.
SUGOU'S A VERY GOOD FRIEND OF
MINE.
I HAVE HIS PERMISSION TO BE HERE
AND WAS JUST ABOUT TO LEAVE
WHEN YOU GRABBED ME.
&gt;&gt; NO ONE TOLD ME YOU WERE GONNA
BE HERE TODAY.
DID YOU KNOW ABOUT HER?
&gt;&gt; UH, NO.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT HE DOESN'T
WANT ANYONE SEEING THIS STUFF
EVER.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
HANG ON A SEC.
THIS IS THE GIRL -- YOU KNOW,
THE ONE SUGOU KEEPS LOCKED UP AT
THE TOP OF THE WORLD TREE.
&gt;&gt; RIGHT. RIGHT.
I HEARD ABOUT HER.
I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR HOW THE
BOSS GETS TO HAVE ALL THE FUN
WITH THIS CUTE GIRL.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AAH!
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON.
STOP STRUGGLING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: STOP IT!
LET ME GO, YOU MONSTER!
&gt;&gt; OH, DON'T BE SO MEAN.
AFTER ALL, YOU INTERRUPTED OUR
DEEP-SENSE MAPPING EXPERIMENT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
SCIENTISTS, RIGHT?!
ALL THIS -- IT'S WRONG!
IT'S ILLEGAL TO MESS WITH
PEOPLE'S MINDS -- ILLEGAL AND
UNETHICAL!
&gt;&gt; WELL, IT'S MORE ETHICAL THAN
STICKING ELECTRICAL PROBES INTO
THE BRAIN OF SOME POOR ANIMAL,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
OUR EXPERIMENTS ARE JUST DREAMS,
THAT'S ALL.
&gt;&gt; HE'S RIGHT.
SOMETIMES WE SHOW THEM THE MOST
WONDERFUL DREAM -- DREAMS YOU
WISH YOU'D NEVER WAKE UP FROM.
I WISH I COULD HAVE THAT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU'RE INSANE.
&gt;&gt; THE BOSS IS OUT ON BUSINESS,
RIGHT?
LOG OUT AND GO SEE WHAT HE WANTS
US TO DO WITH HER.
&gt;&gt; AH, FINE. WHATEVER.
LISTEN, THOUGH -- UNTIL I GET
BACK, DON'T DO ANYTHING I
WOULDN'T DO.
&gt;&gt; OH, YEAH, SURE.
HURRY UP AND GET GOING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTING ]
YOU CAN'T KEEP ME HERE!
PUT ME DOWN RIGHT NOW!
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY, BUT I CAN'T.
THE BOSS WOULD KILL ME IF I LET
YOU GO.
OH, WAIT, I HAVE IT.
WHY DON'T YOU AND I TAKE
ELECTRO-DRUGS?
I'M SO BORED WITH DOLLS, BUT YOU
LOOK LIKE SOMEONE I CAN HAVE FUN
WITH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
STOP IT!
[ GRUNTS ] NO!
STOP!
&gt;&gt; AAAAAAAAAAH!
OKAY!
I'M PUTTING YOU DOWN!
HERE'S ME PUTTING YOU DOWN!
[ GRUNTS ] GEEZ!
NEXT TIME I'LL REMEMBER TO TURN
MY PAIN SENSORS OFF.
&gt;&gt; OKAY. WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
&gt;&gt; HMM? WHAT? NOTHING.
UH, NOTHING HAPPENED.
SO, WHAT DID THE BOSS SAY?
&gt;&gt; OH, HE WAS SO PISSED.
HE SAID WE HAD TO PUT HER BACK
IN THE CAGE UPSTAIRS, CHANGE THE
PASSCODE, AND KEEP AN EYE ON HER
24/7.
&gt;&gt; DAMN IT, DAMN IT, DAMN IT.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO HAVE SOME
FUN.
OKAY. I SAY WE WALK HER BACK
INSTEAD OF TELEPORTING HER.
I WANT TO ENJOY THIS FEELING AS
LONG AS I CAN.
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
YOU'RE A PERV.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; STOP STRUGGLING.
IT WON'T DO YOU ANY GOOD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; DON'T FALL OFF HIM!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LET ME GO!
&gt;&gt; GOOD ONE.
&gt;&gt; SHE'S REALLY PRETTY.
I FEEL SORRY FOR HER THAT SHE
HASN'T WOKEN UP YET.
I DON'T KNOW IF COMING HERE WAS
SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
I'M SO CONFUSED.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL.
I THOUGHT IF I MET HER, I'D
FIGURE IT OUT.
BUT NOW I DON'T KNOW WHAT I
WANT.
DO I WANT TO BE A GOOD
SISTER...
OR...WHAT?
KAZUTO.
[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
I HOPE WE HAVE ANOTHER CHANCE TO
HANG OUT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> Asuna: THIS WON'T STOP ME,
KIRITO -- NO WAY.
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP.
I'LL FIND A WAY TO GET OUT OF
HERE.
&gt;&gt; [ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
[ SIGHS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, LEAFA.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
WHAT'S WRONG? YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; UNH-UNH.
[ CRYING ]
I'M NOT OKAY AT ALL.
I JUST -- I JUST -- I JUST GOT
MY HEART BROKEN!
I...
[ CRYING ]
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I'M TELLING YOU
THIS.
WE JUST MET.
AND I KNOW IT'S NOT COOL FOR
PLAYERS TO DRAG THEIR REAL-LIFE
PROBLEMS INTO THE GAME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S OKAY TO CRY.
DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU'RE HERE OR
IN THE REAL WORLD.
THERE'S NO RULE.
EVEN IN A GAME, YOU CAN SHOW
YOUR FEELINGS IF YOU WANT.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO...
[ CRYING ]
I'M IN LOVE WITH MY BROTHER.
AND THAT'S SOMETHING I CAN'T
TELL ANYONE ABOUT -- EVER.
I HAVE TO BURY THESE FEELINGS
DEEP IN MY HEART.
MAYBE THEN, SOMEDAY, I CAN
FORGET.
[ BELL TOLLING ]
[ CRYING ]
[ TOLLING CONTINUES ]
I'M OKAY NOW.
THANKS FOR THE PEP TALK, KIRITO.
YOU'RE REALLY SWEET.
YOU KNOW THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, YEAH, WELL,
YOU'RE PROBABLY THE ONLY PERSON
WHO THINKS THAT ABOUT ME.
YOU WANT TO LOG OFF FOR TODAY?
I CAN MAKE IT THE REST OF THE
WAY MYSELF.
&gt;&gt; NO.
I MEAN, I'VE COME THIS FAR, SO I
MIGHT AS WELL GO ALL THE WAY.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI, YOU HERE?
&gt;&gt; [ YAWNS ]
GOOD MORNING.
I HOPE YOU BOTH SLEPT WELL.
&gt;&gt; GOOD MORNING, YUI.
HEY, I DIDN'T GET THE CHANCE TO
ASK YOU YESTERDAY, BUT, LIKE, DO
NAVI PIXIES EVER SLEEP?
&gt;&gt; OH, NO.
SEE, WHENEVER DADDY LOGS OUT OF
THE GAME, I SHUT DOWN MY INPUT
CIRCUITS AND PROCESS THE DATA
I'VE ACQUIRED.
YOU COULD CONSIDER IT A LITTLE
LIKE HUMAN SLEEP, BUT IT'S NOT.
&gt;&gt; THEN HOW COME YOU YAWNED?
&gt;&gt; OH. WELL, THAT'S WHAT HUMANS
DO DURING THEIR BOOT-UP
SEQUENCE.
WHEN DADDY YAWNS, IT USUALLY
LASTS FOR EIGHT SECONDS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: PLEASE KEEP THE WEIRD
TRIVIA TO YOURSELF.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CLEARS THROAT ]
YOU READY TO GO?
&gt;&gt; YEP.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
THERE'S TONS OF PEOPLE HERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I GUESS IT REALLY IS
THE CENTER OF ALfheim.
&gt;&gt; IT SEEMS ALL THE FAIRY RACES
THE WORLD OVER ARE HERE.
LOOK HOW THEY'RE ALL GETTING
ALONG.
&gt;&gt; AND HE FLEW RIGHT OFF!
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA.
THERE IT IS -- THE WORLD TREE.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, AND IT LOOKS EVEN MORE
AMAZING UP CLOSE, DOESN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; UM...I HEARD THERE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE A CITY UP THERE AT THE
TOP.
WHAT ELSE?
&gt;&gt; OBERON, THE FAIRY KING, LIVES
THERE, ALONG WITH THE ALF, THE
FAIRIES OF LIGHT.
AND THEY SAY THE FIRST RACE TO
GET TO THE TOP AND SEE THE KING
WILL BECOME AN ALF.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HAS ANYONE EVER TRIED
CLIMBING UP THE SIDE OF THAT
THING?
&gt;&gt; THEY MADE THE WHOLE PERIMETER
OF THE TRUNK OFF LIMITS SO A
PLAYER CAN'T EVEN GET CLOSE
ENOUGH TO TRY.
AND IF YOU JUST FLY STRAIGHT UP,
THE FLIGHT LIMIT OF YOUR WINGS
WOULD EXPIRE BEFORE YOU EVEN GOT
HALFWAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I HEARD ABOUT SOME
PLAYERS WHO TRIED.
THEY GOT MORE THAN HALFWAY UP BY
PIGGYBACKING ON EACH OTHER.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I HEARD ABOUT THEM, ALL
RIGHT, BUT THEY COULD ONLY MAKE
IT UP TO THE LOWEST BRANCHES
BEFORE BAILING.
THE G.M.s FREAKED OUT AND FIXED
IT SO NO ONE COULD EVER DO IT
AGAIN.
KNOW WHAT THEY DID?
THEY PUT A BARRIER UP THERE JUST
ABOVE THE CLOUDS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: INTERESTING.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
LET'S HEAD TO THE BASE OF THE
TRUNK.
&gt;&gt; RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
[ MID-TEMPO ORCHESTRAL MUSIC
PLAYING ]
ONCE WE PASS THROUGH THAT GATE,
WE'RE IN THE WORLD'S HEART --
THE CENTRAL DISTRICT OF ARUN.
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT, YUI?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
&gt;&gt; MOMMY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; IT'S MOMMY! SHE'S HERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPING ]
ARE YOU SURE?
&gt;&gt; YES, I'M POSITIVE!
&gt;&gt; HEY, I --
&gt;&gt; I SCANNED AGAIN, AND IT'S
MOMMY'S PLAYER I.D.!
HER COORDINATES ARE ABOVE US IN
THE TREE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ] WAIT!
KIRITO!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]