&gt;&gt; Kirito: OAS NARZA NOH-TOH
RAISA AUGA.
&gt;&gt; WHOA!
EVERYTHING LOOKS WAY BRIGHTER
NOW!
SO THISIS NIGHT-VISION MAGIC.
I GUESS SPRIGGANS AREGOOD FOR
SOMETHING AFTER ALL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T KNOW IF THAT
WAS A COMPLIMENT OR A DISS.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE PRACTICING THE MAGIC YOU
CAN USE.
THAT'STHE IMPORTANT THING.
AND PROJECTING ILLUSIONS IS ONE
OF YOUR SPECIALTIES.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ILLUSIONS?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, TO TRICK PEOPLE WITH.
IT'S COOL, BUT IT'S NOT GONNA
HELP ANYONE MUCH IN COMBAT.
BUT YOU NEVER KNOW.
IN A LIFE-OR-DEATH SITUATION,
YOUR LAME SPRIGGAN MAGIC MIGHT
ACTUALLY COME IN HANDY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANS ]
NOW, THATWAS A DISS.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SE-AH URAAZA NOH...
NOH-TOH?
&gt;&gt; NO, YOU'RE JUST MEMORIZING
THE WORDS.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN WHAT THE WORDS
OF POWER MEAN FIRST, THEN MATCH
THEM WITH THE EFFECTS OF THE
MAGIC.
THAT'S HOW YOU MEMORIZE SPELLS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UGH!
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D BE IN A GAME
AND HAVE TO MEMORIZE WORDS FROM
A DIFFERENT LANGUAGE.
&gt;&gt; OH, AND JUST SO YOU KNOW,
THE HIGHER-RANKED SPELLS HAVE
ABOUT 20 WORDS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HOLY CRAP.
I'LL JUST STICK TO FIGHTING,
THEN.
&gt;&gt; WOULD YOU QUIT COMPLAINING?
[ BEEPING ]
[ GASPS ]
OH, SOMEONE'S MESSAGING ME.
SORRY -- I HAVE TO GET THIS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SURE.
&gt;&gt; IT'S RECON AGAIN.
IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING, BUT I'LL
CHECK ANYWAY.
IT SAYS, "I WAS RIGHT.
BE CAREFUL. S."
THAT'S IT.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
"S"...
SA...SHI...SU--
OHHHH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; OH...NOTHING.
&gt;&gt; DADDY!
I'M PICKING UP MOVEMENT BEHIND
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ARE THEY MONSTERS?
&gt;&gt; UNH-UNH.
THEY'RE PLAYERS -- A LOT.
12 TOTAL.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE KIDDING.
OHH.
I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING ABOUT
THIS.
WE BETTER TAKE COVER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, BUT WHERE?
&gt;&gt; HA!
JUST LEAVE EVERYTHING TO ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY! EASY!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
SHICK SHAALU OHBIS GROWN
LOPUTOH!
We can talk, but we have to be
really quiet about it.
Anything louder than a whisper,
and it's gonna break the spell.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: Okay.
&gt;&gt; They'll be coming into view
soon.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: What is that?
You see it?
&gt;&gt; Huh?
No, I can't see anything.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I can tell it's not a
player.
It's got red eyes --
kind of like a bat.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY'D YOU BREAK OUR
COVER?
&gt;&gt; BECAUSE THAT THING OUT
THERE'S A HIGH-LEVEL TRACING
SEARCHER!
WE HAVE TO DESTROY IT!
EKKU SKEETOH TUTOOGUE SUMAHL
STREEDA!
COME ON! WE GOT TO GO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CAN'T WE JUST HIDE
BEHIND ONE OF YOUR SPELLS AGAIN?
&gt;&gt; THEY ALREADY KNOW WE'RE HERE.
THAT TRACER HAD US PEGGED.
HIDING'S NOT GONNA DO US ANY
GOOD.
BESIDES, THAT BAT WAS A
FIRE ELEMENT FAMILIAR.
THAT CAN ONLY MEAN THE ONES
WHO ARE TRACKING US ARE...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THE SALAMANDERS.
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S A PARTY OF SALAMANDERS
DOING WAY DOWN HERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA!
CHECK OUT THE LAKE!
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA GET AWAY!
&gt;&gt; WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOING, OR
YOU'LL FALL IN!
OH, CRAP!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, DAMN IT!
[ GRUNTS ]
UNH!
[ GROANS ]
&gt;&gt; THAT WON'T WORK.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL
ME THAT BEFORE?
>> OH, RIGHT -- LIKE IT'S MY
FAULT YOU'RE IN A HURRY.
IT'S AN EARTH-MAGIC BARRIER,
YOU CAN BASH ON IT ALL DAY, AND
IT WON'T DESTROY IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CAN WE JUMP IN THE
LAKE AND SWIM AROUND IT?
&gt;&gt; NOPE.
AT LEAST, NOT UNLESS YOU WANT TO
BE LUNCH.
THE WATER'S FILLED WITH
HIGH-LEVEL MONSTERS.
THE UNDINES ARE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN TAKE THOSE KINDS OF
THINGS ON.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN I GUESS THE ONLY
OPTION LEFT IS TO FIGHT.
&gt;&gt; I'M NOT GONNA ARGUE WITH
THAT, BUT IT WON'T BE EASY.
IF THE SALAMANDERS HAVE
HIGH-LEVEL EARTH MAGIC, IT CAN
ONLY MEAN ONE THING -- THEY HAVE
A POWERFUL MAGE ON THEIR SIDE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LEAFA...
I KNOW YOU'RE GOOD WITH A SWORD,
SO DON'T TAKE THIS THE WRONG
WAY, BUT COULD YOU BACK ME UP
FROM HERE ON IN?
I NEED YOU TO STAY BEHIND AND
FOCUS ON HEALING ME.
THAT WAY, I CAN FIGHT HARDER AND
NOT WORRY ABOUT MY HP.
[ SHOUTS ]
>>THEY'RE TARGETING HIM WITH
EVERYTHING THEY GOT!
&gt;&gt; All: LEEZA FORUK!
RANDOL DOROTOH!
&gt;&gt; KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
&gt;&gt; SOO FILLAH HAYDL ASTALOO
PROT-TO SU-PAAL BHAA-NI!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; UH-OH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SHOUTS ]
&gt;&gt; PROTTOH SUPAAL BAANI!
WHAT DO WE DO?
HE'S GONNA RUN OUT OF HP AT
SOME POINT!
THAT'S ENOUGH, KIRITO!
IF WE LOSE, IT'LL JUST MEAN A
COUPLE EXTRA HOURS OF FLYING!
LET'S GIVE UP WHILE WE CAN!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO WAY.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AS LONG AS I'M ALIVE,
I'M NOT GONNA LET ANYONE IN MY
PARTY DIE.
I WON'TLET THAT HAPPEN AGAIN!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT THE HELL?!
WHAT'S HE DOING?!
&gt;&gt; HURRY!
THIS IS YOUR ONLY CHANCE!
&gt;&gt; WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE TO USE ALL THE MANA
YOU HAVE!
HURRY AND FOCUS ON SHIELDING HIM
FROM THE NEXT MAGIC ATTACK!
&gt;&gt; UH, OKAY.
BUT I DON'T THINK IT'S GONNA
HELP.
&gt;&gt; All: EKKU BALPA EH-IN
BRANDOH MUSPEEEEK KARRAH
BREASTA.
&gt;&gt; SOO SHALU LINDOH ASHEE-NYA
BAATOH AIMEE OH-GU!
&gt;&gt; All: BAA-NI STAY-PAH.
&gt;&gt; SVELDOH!
&gt;&gt; RAAHN-DOL DORO-TOH!
&gt;&gt; DO IT NOW, DADDY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SE-AH URAAZA NO-TOH
DEEPTOH!
&gt;&gt; HE'S USING ILLUSION MAGIC.
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; BUT ALL THAT'S GONNA DO IS
MAKE HIM LOOK LIKE A GIANT
MONSTER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
&gt;&gt; IS THAT...KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ ROARING ]
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; IDIOTS!
DON'T BREAK FORMATION!
IT'S NOT REAL!
DON'T BE AFRAID!
HE CAN'T HURT US IF YOU STICK TO
THE PLAN AND STAY IN FORMATION!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERS ]
HIT HIM WITH AN EXPLOSION SPELL!
&gt;&gt; All: ECKU BALPA!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; [ Nervously ] EH-HAN!
[ SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; YAY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROWLS ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
[ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; RETREAT! RETREAT!
RETRE-E-E-E-E-AT!!
AAH! AAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
NO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROWLING SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; STOP!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
WAIT, KIRITO!
HOLD ON! DON'T KILL HIM!
&gt;&gt; ISN'T MY DADDY AMAZING?!
&gt;&gt; OW, MY --
AAH!
&gt;&gt; OKAY, IF YOU WANT TO LIVE,
YOU BETTER TELL ME WHO SENT YOU
ASS-HATS AFTER US.
&gt;&gt; NEVER.
KILL ME IF YOU WANT!
&gt;&gt; YOU GOT IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Laughing ] OH, MAN!
NOW, THAT WAS COOL!
THAT WAS AN AWESOME FIGHT!
&gt;&gt; HEHHH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOUR PLAN WASN'T
SHABBY, EITHER.
IF I WAS ALONE, I WOULDN'T HAVE
LASTED A MINUTE AGAINST YOU
DORKS.
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU TELLING HIM THAT
FOR?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LET ME HANDLE THIS.
LISTEN UP.
I WANT TO SEE IF YOU AND ME CAN
MAKE A DEAL.
CHECK IT OUT.
THOSE ARE ALL THE ITEMS AND YULD
I WON AFTER BEATING YOUR ASSES.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ANSWER MY
QUESTIONS, AND THEY COULD BE
YOURS.
SOUND GOOD?
&gt;&gt; SERIOUSLY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: TOTALLY.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
&gt;&gt; UGH. MEN.
M IT'S LIKE THEY FORGOT WE'RE
EVEN HERE.
&gt;&gt; EARLIER THIS EVENING, I GOT
AN URGENT TEXT FROM G-TAKUSU.
HE'S THE LEADER OF THE MAGE
SQUAD -- OR USEDTO BE.
ANYWAY, I GOT THIS TEXT TELLING
US ALL TO MEET HIM HERE.
AND WHEN I SHOWED UP, HE SAID HE
NEEDED 12 OF US TO GO ON A HUNT
FOR TWO PLAYERS.
AT FIRST, I THOUGHT IT WAS
OVERKILL, BUT, WELL, HE SAID YOU
GUYS TOOK OUT KAGEMUNE, SO IT
MADE SENSE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHO'S THIS KAGEMUNE
GUY?
&gt;&gt; HE'S THE LEADER OF THE LANCER
SQUAD, AND HE'S KNOWN FOR
HUNTING SYLPHS.
YESTERDAY, HE GOT CREAMED IN
A FIGHT AND HAD TO RETREAT.
THAT WAS YOU GUYS, WASN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; WAIT.
WHY'S G-TAKUSU SO INTERESTED IN
GETTING US OUT OF THE WAY?
&gt;&gt; THE ORDER CAME FROM THE TOP.
SOMETHING ABOUT YOU "INTERFERING
WITH THE PLAN."
>> Kirito: YEAH? WHATPLAN?
&gt;&gt; [ Chuckling ] HEY, I'M JUST A
GRUNT.
THEY DON'T TELL ME ANYTHING.
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE SOMETHING
REALLY BIG'S ABOUT TO GO DOWN.
WHEN I LOGGED ON TODAY, I SAW
THIS BIG-ASS SWARM OF SALAMANDER
TROOPS HEADING UP NORTH.
&gt;&gt; NO WAY.
THEY'RE GONNA GO TRY TO CLEAR
THE WORLD TREE, AREN'T THEY?
&gt;&gt; I DOUBT THAT.
SOMEONE FIGURED THAT TO TAKE THE
TREE, THE WHOLE ARMY WOULD NEED
ANCIENT-WEAPON-CLASS EQUIPMENT,
AND WE CAN'T AFFORD THAT STUFF.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S EVERYTHING I KNOW.
I PROMISE.
You weren't lying about your end
of the deal, were you?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO.
I'M A MAN OF MY WORD, PARTNER.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUMBLES ]
HEY.
THAT BIG, UGLY MONSTER THAT
WAS TEARING EVERYTHING UP --
WAS THAT YOU OR AN ILLUSION?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH...
I DON'T REMEMBER.
&gt;&gt; WAIT -- YOU DON'T KNOW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOT REALLY.
IT JUST HAPPENS SOMETIMES.
IN THE HEAT OF BATTLE, I'LL SNAP
AND CAN'T REMEMBER A THING
AFTER.
&gt;&gt; WHOA. SCARY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I THINK I REMEMBER
MOST OF WHAT HAPPENED THIS LAST
TIME, THOUGH.
LIKE, I KNOW I USED THAT SPELL
YUI SUGGESTED.
&gt;&gt; DO IT NOW!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I ALSO REMEMBER
GETTING HUGE.
THAT WAS COOL.
I REMEMBER LOSING MY SWORD AND
THEN...GRABBING PEOPLE.
&gt;&gt; AND YOU WERE CHOMPING DOWN ON
THEM.
REMEMBER THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Chuckling ] OH,
YEAH.
I TOTALLY FELT LIKE A MONSTER --
ALL EATING PEOPLE AND
EVERYTHING.
&gt;&gt; SO, UH...WHAT DID THEY TASTE
LIKE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: KINDA LIKE GRILLED
MEAT JUST BEFORE IT GETS
BURNT -- ALL CRISPY AND --
&gt;&gt; OKAY, GOOD! SORRY I ASKED!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
[ CHOMPS ]
&gt;&gt; AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ SMACK ]
WOW!
SO, THIS IS LEGRUE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OW! THAT HURT.
&gt;&gt; THEN YOU SHOULDN'T BE BITING
PEOPLE.
&gt;&gt; I'LL SAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY IS EVERYONE
GANGING UP ON ME?
I WAS TRYING TO BREAK THE
TENSION WITH A STUPID JOKE, IS
ALL.
&gt;&gt; BITE ME AGAIN, AND I'LL CUT
YOU IN HALF.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
YES, MA'AM.
&gt;&gt; UGH.
OH, LOOK!
[ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, I JUST
REMEMBERED SOMETHING.
&gt;&gt; HMM?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: RIGHT BEFORE THOSE
SALAMANDERS ATTACKED US, YOU GOT
A MESSAGE FROM YOUR FRIEND.
&gt;&gt; OH! I TOTALLY FORGOT!
RECON'S NOT ONLINE.
MAYBE HE'S ASLEEP.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, WELL, WHY
DON'T YOU LOG OUT AND GIVE HIM A
CALL?
&gt;&gt; HMM.
YEAH, I THINK I BETTER CHECK IN
WITH HIM.
I'LL ONLY BE GONE A SEC.
WAIT FOR ME HERE, OKAY?
YUI, WOULD YOU PLEASE KEEP AN
EYE ON MY AVATAR?
&gt;&gt; ME?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I NEED TO MAKE SURE
YOUR DAD DOESN'T MESS AROUND
WITH IT WHILE I'M OUT.
&gt;&gt; COPY THAT, MA'AM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU GOT TO BE
KIDDING.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS GROGGILY ]
[ GASPS ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGING ]
[ BEEP ]
HEY, NAGATA.
WHAT'S WITH ALL THE CALLS?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
&gt;&gt; You picked up! Finally!
Where were you, Suguha?
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
I WAS DEALING WITH SOME IN-GAME
STUFF.
&gt;&gt; W-We got trouble!
Like -- like big trouble!
Sigurd's coming after us!
A-And that's not all!
He betrayed Sakuya, the Sylph
commander!
&gt;&gt; BETRAYED HER?
HOW?
START FROM THE BEGINNING AND
TELL ME EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENED.
&gt;&gt; But we're running out of
time!
[ Sighing ] Okay.
Remember when the Salamanders
ambushed us in the
Ancient Forest?
Well, didn't that whole setup
seem a little...weird to you?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW. NOT REALLY.
WHY DO YOU THINK IT WAS WEIRD?
&gt;&gt; Remember how Sigurd said he'd
be the decoy and then he lured
three of them away?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, NOW THAT YOU MENTION
&gt;&gt; Don't you think it was out of
character?
I mean, usually, he'd make
someone else do it, right?
&gt;&gt; YEAH...I GUESS.
I MEAN, YOU'RE RIGHT -- IT'S
WEIRD -- BUT WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
[ RAIN FALLING ]
&gt;&gt; Okay, here it is.
I found out he's been working as
a spy for the Salamanders --
probably for a while now.
&gt;&gt; WHAT?!
DO YOU HAVE PROOF, OR DID YOU
JUST HEAR ABOUT IT?
&gt;&gt; Remember how I said something
was bugging me?
Well, I used a transparency
spell, and I've been following
Sigurd all day.
I TRACKED HIM TO A BACK
ALLEY.
AND I SAW HIM AND A COUPLE
OTHERS PUT ON INVISIBILITY
CLOAKS.
THEY WERE UP TOSOMETHING.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
I FOLLOWED THEM DOWN INTO THE
SEWERS, WHERE THESE TWO SKETCHY
GUYS WERE WAITING FOR THEM.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY WERE SALAMANDERS!
THEY WERE A LITTLE WAYS AWAY
FROM ME, SO I COULDN'T HEAR
EVERYTHING.
BUT I HEARD THE SALAMANDERS SAY
THEY PUT A TRACER ON YOU.
UHHH!
[ SQUEALS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; KEEP GOING.
THEN WHAT?
&gt;&gt; The Salamanders caught me.
I'm still in the sewers,
paralyzed by the poison arrow.
&gt;&gt; WELL, NOW I KNOW WHY YOU KEPT
CALLING ME I.R.L.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
&gt;&gt; There's something else.
Sakuya is supposed to form an
alliance with the Cait Sith
today.
The meeting's in neutral
territory, and she's heading
there right now -- in secret.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Sigurd knows about it, too.
He's gonna show up at the
signing ceremony with his goons
and attack it!
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AHHH...
&gt;&gt; WE HAVE TO HURRY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
HEY, WELCOME BACK, LEAFA.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, WELCOME BACK.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO, I HAVE TO LEAVE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY?
&gt;&gt; SORRY, BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF RIGHT
AWAY.
IF I HAD TIME TO EXPLAIN,
BELIEVE ME, I WOULD.
BUT I CAN'T.
AND I DON'T THINK I'LL BE COMING
BACK HERE, EITHER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN I GUESS YOU'LL
JUST HAVE TO EXPLAIN IT ME ON
THE WAY.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'LL TAKE A WHILE TO
GET OUT OF HERE 'CAUSE WE CAN'T
FLY.
THAT'S ENOUGH TIME, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, RIGHT.
40 MINUTES FROM NOW, IN THE
VALLEY OF THE BUTTERFLIES, THE
LEADERS OF THE SYLPHS AND THE
CAIT SITHS ARE GONNA HAVE A
MEETING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MIND IF I ASK A
COUPLE QUESTIONS BEFORE WE GET
THERE?
&gt;&gt; GO AHEAD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF THE SALAMANDERS
ATTACK THE SYLPHS AND THE
CAIT SITHS, WHAT ARE THEYGONNA
GET OUT OF IT?
&gt;&gt; FOR ONE, THEY'D STOP THE
ALLIANCE FROM HAPPENING.
AND IF THE CAIT SITHS FIND OUT
THEIR LEADER DIED BECAUSE A
SYLPH TURNED TRAITOR, THEY'D BE
PRETTY PISSED, WOULDN'T THEY?
>> Kirito: SUPERPISSED.
&gt;&gt; IT'S A GOOD WAY TO START A
WAR BETWEEN THE CAIT SITHS AND
THE SYLPHS, THAT'S FOR SURE.
IT'S ALSO A GOOD WAY TO GET
RICH.
IF YOU TAKE OUT THE LEADER OF A
TERRITORY, YOU GET 30% OF ITS
MONEY.
YOU CAN INVADE ITS HOMETOWN
FOR 10 DAYS AND CHARGE WHATEVER
TAX YOU WANT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO WAY.
REALLY?
&gt;&gt; SERIOUSLY!
WOULD I LIE TO YOU?
THIS ISN'T YOUR PROBLEM, KIRITO.
IT'S A SYLPH PROBLEM.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY REASON TO GET
INVOLVED AND RISK YOUR LIFE OVER
IF WE GO TO THE MEETING, CHANCES
ARE WE WON'T MAKE IT BACK ALIVE.
AND WE'LL PROBABLY HAVE TO START
OVER FROM SYLVAIN AGAIN.
BUT...THIS COULD WORK FOR YOU.
YOU WANT TO GET TO THE TOP OF
THE WORLD TREE, SO...YOU MIGHT
BE BETTER OFF WORKING WITH THE
SALAMANDERS.
IF THEY CAN PULL THIS OFF, IT'LL
GIVE THEM THE POWER AND
RESOURCES THEY NEED TO MAKE AN
ATTEMPT AT THE WORLD TREE.
AND SINCE YOU'RE A SPRIGGAN,
THEY MIGHT HIRE YOU AS A
MERCENARY.
SO...IF YOU WANTED TO KILL ME,
YOU COULD.
I WOULDN'T HOLD IT AGAINST YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S JUST A GAME IN
THE END.
ANYTHING GOES, RIGHT?
IF YOU WANT TO KILL, YOU KILL.
IF YOU WANT TO STEAL, YOU STEAL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE THINK LIKE THAT.
MORE THAN I CARE TO KNOW.
AND IN A WAY, I GET IT.
EVEN I USED TO THINK LIKE THAT.
BUT NONE OF IT'S TRUE.
IN A VIRTUAL WORLD, THERE'S
THINGS YOU HAVE TO PROTECT
BECAUSEIT'S A VIRTUAL WORLD.
SOMEONE SPECIAL TAUGHT ME THAT.
IF YOU GIVE IN TO YOUR IMPULSES
IN HERE, IT'S GONNA CHANGE WHO
YOU ARE IN THE REAL WORLD.
THE PLAYER AND THE CHARACTER ARE
ONE AND THE SAME.
LEAFA...YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON.
AND I WANT TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT THE
REASON IS -- THERE'S NO WAY IN
HELL I'D EVER ATTACK A FRIEND
FOR MY OWN BENEFIT.
I COULDN'T LIVE WITH MYSELF.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO, I...
THANK YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. WOW.
I SOUNDED PRETENTIOUS, DIDN'T I?
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
&gt;&gt; UNH-UNH.
THAT WAS PRETTY COOL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, CRAP!
WE'RE WASTING TIME JUST STANDING
HERE.
WE GOT TO GO.
YUI, LEAD THE WAY.
&gt;&gt; YOU GOT IT, DADDY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HERE -- GIVE ME YOUR
HAND.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, BUT, UH --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME ON!
&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPS ]
M-MONSTERS!
[ CREATURES SNARLING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE'S THE EXIT!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]