&gt;&gt; [ Panting ] ASUNA.
[ PANTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE LATE, KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
WHO'S THERE?
&gt;&gt; I'VE BEEN OUT HERE SO LONG.
I MIGHT CATCH COLD.
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] SUGOU!
&gt;&gt; YOU DID A VERY BAD THING,
KIRITO.
YOU KNOW, I CAN STILL FEEL THE
PAIN.
&gt;&gt; IT'S OVER, SUGOU.
YOU BETTER TURN YOURSELF IN.
YOU'RE FINISHED.
&gt;&gt; FINISHED?
HARDLY.
THERE ARE LOTS OF COMPANIES THAT
WOULD KILL TO HAVE ME AND MY
RESEARCH, AND ONCE IT'S
COMPLETE, THERE WON'T BE
ANYTHING OR ANYONE STANDING IN
MY WAY.
THEN I'LL BE THE GOD OF THIS
WORLD.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; OH, BUT FIRST -- FIRST, I'M
GOING TO KILL YOU.
KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; COME ON, GET UP.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; I SAID, "GET UP"!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU THINK A PIECE OF TRASH
LIKE YOU CAN GET IN MY WAY?
DID YOU THINK I'D LET YOU SLOW
ME DOWN?
WANT TO KNOW WHAT THE PUNISHMENT
DEATH.
I WON'T ACCEPT ANYTHING LESS.
DAMN.
MY RIGHT EYE IS ALL FOGGY.
BUT I WON'T MISS AGAIN --
PROMISE.
YOU...BASTARD!
YOU LITTLE BOY, YOU'RE A PIECE
OF SCUM!
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY REAL POWER!
&gt;&gt; AND NEITHER DO YOU,
SUGOU.
&gt;&gt; DIE, DAMN YOU!!
&gt;&gt; AAH!
AAH!
SUCH A WEAK WEAPON -- TOO LIGHT,
NO REACH -- AND IT'S ALL I'M
GONNA NEED TO KILL YOU ONCE AND
FOR ALL.
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERING ]
AAH!
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
&gt;&gt; [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERING ]
[ KNIFE CLATTERS ]
>>HURRY UP -- SHE'S WAITING FOR
YOU!
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS SOFTLY ]
ASUNA.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; IT'S OKAY NOW.
IT'S OVER.
I FOUGHT THE FINAL BOSS JUST
NOW, AND THE LAST BATTLE'S OVER.
[ Voice breaking ] IT'S ALL
OVER.
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY, BUT I CAN'T HEAR
TOO WELL RIGHT NOW.
I THINK I KNOW WHAT YOU SAID
THOUGH, WHAT YOU MEANT -- THAT
IT'S REALLY OVER.
AND FINALLY -- FINALLY -- I GET
TO MEET YOU.
SO, ANYWAY, I'M ASUNA --
ASUNA YUKI.
AND I'M FINALLY BACK.
&gt;&gt; [ SNIFFLES ]
I'M KAZUTO KIRIGAYA.
WELCOME HOME, ASUNA.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; LOOKING AT THIS SENTENCE,
COULD ANYONE TELL ME HOW --
[ BELL TOLLS ]
WELL, LOOKS LIKE THAT'S ALL FOR
TODAY.
KEEP AN EYE OUT FOR HOMEWORK
FILES 25 AND 26, THEN MAKE SURE
TO UPLOAD YOUR ANSWERS BY NEXT
WEEK.
[ STUDENTS GROAN ]
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; THANKS FOR WAITING FOR ME.
[ SIGHS ]
I'M TIRED -- TIRED AND HUNGRY.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE STARTING TO SOUND LIKE
AN OLD MAN, KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, WELL, I FEEL LIKE I'VE
GOTTEN ABOUT FIVE YEARS OLDER IN
THE LAST MONTH.
AND, BY THE WAY, IT'S NOT
KIRITO.
IT'S KAZUTO.
THIS IS REAL LIFE.
YOU SHOULDN'T CALL SOMEONE BY
THEIR AVATAR'S NAME HERE.
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY! I FORGOT.
OH, NO, NOW WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
EVERYONE WILL KNOW IT'S ME.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR USING
YOUR REAL NAME FOR YOUR AVATAR.
EH, I GUESS IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER 'CAUSE EVERYONE AT OUR
SCHOOL IS STUCK IN S.A.O. SAME
AS US.
MY COVER'S PROBABLY BLOWN, TOO.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; ASUNA, ARE YOU GETTING AROUND
OKAY?
I MEAN, IS THE REHAB YOU'RE
DOING HELPING?
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
I FINALLY GOT THE OKAY TO WALK
AROUND WITHOUT MY CRUTCHES,
ALTHOUGH THE DOCTORS SAY I
SHOULDN'T RUN JUST YET.
&gt;&gt; YOU WILL.
&gt;&gt; BY THE WAY, KIRITO...
&gt;&gt; WHAT?
&gt;&gt; ...DO YOU KNOW THAT EVERYONE
IN THE CAFETERIA CAN SEE US?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; SERIOUSLY.
THAT LITTLE OVERSIGHT IS GONNA
COST YOU LUNCH.
&gt;&gt; SORRY!
I DIDN'T KNOW.
&gt;&gt; TA-DA!
&gt;&gt; [ GULPS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
I WAS WONDERING ABOUT YOUR DAD.
IS HE OKAY?
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
HE IS, BUT HE'S STILL NOT OVER
THIS WHOLE THING.
HE QUIT AS C.E.O. AND TOOK AN
EARLY RETIREMENT.
AND NOW THAT HE'S GOT ALL THIS
FREE TIME, HE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO WITH IT.
HOPEFULLY, DAD CAN FIND A HOBBY,
AND MAYBE THAT'LL CHEER HIM UP.
&gt;&gt; I HOPE SO.
THAT NIGHT IN THE PARKING LOT,
THE POLICE CAME AND ARRESTED
SUGOU.
LATER, WHEN THEY INTERROGATED
HIM, HE DENIED EVERYTHING AND
TRIED TO PIN THE BLAME ON
AKIHIKO KAYABA.
BUT AFTER THE POLICE QUESTIONED
ONE OF HIS EMPLOYEES, SUGOU
CONFESSED TO EVERYTHING.
AS FOR THOSE 300 S.A.O.
PLAYERS, WHEN THEY CAME TO,
THEY COULDN'T REMEMBER ANYTHING
ABOUT THE EXPERIMENTS.
THE GOOD THING IS THEY DIDN'T
SUFFER ANY NEUROLOGICAL OR
PSYCHIATRIC AFTER EFFECTS, SO
EVERYONE CAN GO BACK TO THEIR
LIVES.
BUT THE FATE OF VIRTUAL MMOs
WAS A DIFFERENT STORY.
THIS LATEST INCIDENT
PRACTICALLY DESTROYED THE
INDUSTRY ALL TOGETHER.
IN THE END, RCT PROGRESS WAS
DISMANTLED.
ITS PARENT COMPANY ALSO
SUFFERED A BIG HIT.
A.L.O. WAS SHUT DOWN -- NO
SURPRISE THERE.
AND AS FOR THE FIVE OR SIX
OTHER VRMMOs, WITH ALL THE
NEGATIVE PRESS AND THE PUBLIC
OUTCRY, THEIR DAYS WERE
NUMBERED, TOO.
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW WHO I WAS JUST
THINKING ABOUT?
THE COMMANDER.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
&gt;&gt; HMM? OH.
YEAH.
KAYABA'S DEAD.
THEY SAY IT WAS SUICIDE.
&gt;&gt; NO WAY.
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
WHEN THE WORLD OF S.A.O.
COLLAPSED, HE DID A HIGH-OUTPUT
SCAN ON HIS BRAIN AND FRIED IT
WHEN IT WAS OVER.
&gt;&gt; SO, WAIT.
WAS HE TRYING TO COPY HIS
CONSCIOUSNESS TO THE NET OR
SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; WELL, IT'S A
ONE-IN-A-THOUSAND SHOT FOR IT TO
WORK, BUT I KNOW HE PULLED IT
OFF.
THAT DAY, KAYABA SPOKE TO ME, OR
HIS CONSCIOUSNESS DID ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S THIS?
&gt;&gt; THE BEGINNINGS OF A NEW
WORLD.
I CALL IT THE SEED.
ONCE IT SPROUTS, YOU'LL KNOW
WHAT IT IS.
WHAT YOU DO WITH IT IS UP TO
YOU.
YOU CAN EVEN DELETE IT IF YOU
WANT.
HOWEVER, IF YOU STILL HAVE A
TINY BIT OF FONDNESS LEFT FOR
THE VIRTUAL WORLD, YOU'LL TAKE
CARE OF IT.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO?
KIRITO, DON'T FORGET -- WE'RE
MEETING THE OTHERS LATER.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
SORRY.
I WAS SPACING OUT.
&gt;&gt; AS ALWAYS.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHETHER YOU'RE
IN THE GAME OR IRL.
THE MINUTE YOU RELAX, YOU SPACE
OUT LIKE A CHAMP.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ BOTH SIGH ]
&gt;&gt; [ SLURPING ]
&gt;&gt; SERIOUSLY.
[ SIGHS ]
RIKA, YOU'RE DRIVING ME CRAZY
WITH ALL THAT SLURPING.
&gt;&gt; LEAVE ME ALONE.
HE'S ALL OVER HER, AND IT'S
DRIVING ME NUTS.
ACTING LIKE THAT AT SCHOOL, IT'S
SO TACKY.
[ SLURPING ]
&gt;&gt; SPYING ON THEM'S KIND OF
TACKY, TOO, YOU KNOW?
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
IF I'D HAVE KNOWN IT WAS GONNA
BE LIKE THIS, I WOULDN'T HAVE
LET YOU TALK ME INTO A
MONTH-LONG TRUCE.
&gt;&gt; I DIDN'T TALK YOU INTO IT!
IT WAS YOURIDEA!
YOU SAID WE SHOULD LET THEM
HAVE THEIR LITTLE ROMANCE FOR A
MONTH, REMEMBER?
I MEAN, GOD, TALK ABOUT NAIVE.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUMBLES ]
IT'S GONNA BE COOL MEETING
EVERYONE TODAY, ISN'T IT?
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I CAN'T WAIT!
&gt;&gt; SUGU.
I FORGOT TO ASK BEFORE -- DID
YOU EVER MEET AGIL?
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
WE WENT HUNTING TOGETHER A
COUPLE OF TIMES IN A.L.O.
HIS AVATAR IS GINORMOUS!
&gt;&gt; YEAH?
WELL, GET READY 'CAUSE HE'S THAT
BIG IN REAL LIFE, TOO.
PREPARE TO HAVE YOUR MIND BLOWN.
[ JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ ALL CHUCKLE ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
&gt;&gt; HOLD ON A SEC.
WERE WE SUPPOSED TO GET HERE
EARLIER?
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
WE GAVE YOU A LATER TIME TO MAKE
SURE EVERYONE ELSE GOT HERE
FIRST.
IT WOULDN'T BE RIGHT FOR THE
GUESTS OF HONOR TO SHOW UP
BEFORE ALL THE GUESTS.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
COME ON IN.
&gt;&gt; UH, HEY --
&gt;&gt; OKAY, LET'S GET THIS PARTY
STARTED.
YOU ALL KNOW WHAT TO DO.
READY, AND...
&gt;&gt; All: CONGRATULATIONS ON
BEATING S.A.O., KIRITO!
[ NOISEMAKERS POPPING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; CHEERS!
&gt;&gt; All: CHEERS!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ SLOW-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
BARTENDER, BOURBON ON THE ROCKS.
[ ICE CLINKS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; WHOA, DUDE.
THIS IS OOLONG TEA.
&gt;&gt; AGIL, SLIDE ME A BIG-BOY
DRINK.
&gt;&gt; KLEIN, SERIOUSLY?
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO GO BACK
TO WORK?
&gt;&gt; [ GULPS, SIGHS ]
ALCOHOL MAKES THE OVERTIME GO BY
FASTER.
UH-OH.
CHICK ALERT.
[ GIRLS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
&gt;&gt; LONG TIME, NO SEE.
&gt;&gt; HI, THINKER.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
I HEARD THAT YOU AND YULIER ARE
MARRIED NOW.
I KNOW IT'S LATE, BUT CONGRATS.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
[ GLASSES CLINK ]
THANK YOU.
BUT EVER SINCE WE GOT BACK, IT'S
BEEN TAKING EVERYTHING WE'VE GOT
TO ADJUST TO LIFE HERE.
THE GOOD THING IS I'M SETTLING
IN TO WORK MODE AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; CONGRATULATIONS ON GETTING
THAT FAR.
HEY, I'VE BEEN READING THE NEW
MMO TODAY.
NICE JOB.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I WISH IT WERE BETTER.
IT COULD HAVE USED A BIT MORE
CONTENT.
OH, WELL.
WITH THE WAY MMOs ARE NOW, WHO
NEEDS WALKTHROUGHS AND NEWS?
THOSE THINGS ARE GONNA BE
IRRELEVANT SOON ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY ABOUT
HOW THE UNIVERSE WAS BORN --
FIRST, THERE WAS CHAOS.
BY THE WAY, AGIL, HAS THE SEED
BEEN DOING OKAY?
&gt;&gt; IT'S DOING AMAZING.
WE GOT 50 MIRRORS ALREADY SET
IT'S BEEN DOWNLOADED 100,000
TIMES.
AND CHECK THIS OUT -- IT'S GOT
300 BIG-ASS SERVERS ACTUALLY
RUNNING IT.
>>AFTER I VISITED ASUNA AT THE
HOSPITAL, I TOOK THE THING
KAYABA CALLED THE SEED OVER TO
AGIL AND ASKED HIM TO CHECK IT
OUT.
TURNED OUT IT WAS A FULL-DIVE
MMO THAT KAYABA DEVELOPED.
IT CAME IN A PROGRAM PACKAGE
CALLED THE WORLD SEED, A
STRIPPED-DOWN VERSION OF THE
CARDINAL SYSTEM THAT COULD RUN
ON SMALL SERVERS.
KAYABA HAD MODIFIED THE PROGRAM
SO THAT ANYONE WITH ACCESS TO
AN ORDINARY SERVER COULD EASILY
DOWNLOAD IT AND USE IT TO
CREATE THEIR VERY OWN ONLINE
WORLD.
AFTER AGIL SAID IT WAS SAFE TO
USE, I HAD HIM UPLOAD IT TO
SERVERS ACROSS THE GLOBE SO
THAT EVERYONE COULD ACCESS IT
FOR FREE.
IT TURNED OUT THAT WAS EXACTLY
WHAT VIRTUAL MMOs NEEDED TO
KEEP THE GENRE GOING.
AS FOR ALfheim ONLINE, ALL THE
DATA WAS TRANSFERRED TO A NEW
COMPANY THAT DECIDED TO KEEP IT
ONLINE AND RUNNING.
BUT THE NEW ALfheim WASN'T THE
THE ONLY WORLD BORN OUT OF THE
SEED.
EVERYONE FROM INDIVIDUAL GAMERS
TO A FEW HUNDRED SMALL
COMPANIES WERE SUDDENLY
CREATING BRAND-NEW WORLDS ON
THEIR VERY OWN VIRTUAL GAME
SERVERS.
THE BEST PART IS THEY WERE ALL
CONNECTED TO EACH OTHER.
IT'S ALMOST TO THE POINT WHERE
YOU COULD CREATE A CHARACTER IN
ONE WORLD, THEN TRANSFER IT TO
ANOTHER WITH ALL ITS SKILLS
INTACT.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; HEY.
HAS ANYTHING CHANGED FOR
TONIGHT'S AFTER PARTY?
&gt;&gt; NOPE.
WE'RE STILL ON FOR 11:00.
WE'RE MEETING UP IN
YGGDRASIL CITY.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU KNOW, I HAD A
FEELING YOU WERE GONNA FLY TOO
HIGH UP.
IT'S ALMOST 11:00, SO I CAME TO
GET YOU.
&gt;&gt; OH. OKAY, THANKS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; HEY, KAZUT-- KIRITO, YOU KNOW
HOW A.L.O.'s GOT A NEW COMPANY
RUNNING IT NOW AND HOW YOU CAN
USE YOUR OLD S.A.O. AVATAR IF
YOU WANT?
EVERYONE ELSE IS USING THEIROLD
AVATAR, SO HOW COME YOU'RE NOT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
I GUESS 'CAUSE, IN THAT WORLD,
THAT KIRITO'S MISSION IS OVER
NOW.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
I GUESS SO.
THEN I WAS THE FIRST TO MEET THE
SPRIGGAN VERSION OF KIRITO AND
SHOW HIM THE WAY TO THE
WORLD TREE.
THAT'S PRETTY COOL.
HEY, KIRITO, DANCE WITH ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; DANCE!
IT'S AN ADVANCED TECHNIQUE I
JUST MASTERED.
YOU JUST HOVER, THEN SLOWLY SPIN
ON YOUR "X" AXIS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; THAT'S IT.
[ CHUCKLES ] YEAH, YOU'RE DOING
GREAT.
[ ENCHANTING MUSIC PLAYS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LEAFA?
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS, SNIFFLES ]
ANYWAY, I THINK I'M GONNA GO
HOME NOW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT W-WHY?
&gt;&gt; [ Voice breaking ] BECAUSE...
IT'S TOO FAR AWAY, LIKE
EVERYTHING AND EVERYONE ELSE,
AND EVEN YOU.
I COULDN'T GO THAT FAR EVEN IF I
TRIED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SUGU.
THAT'S SO NOT TRUE.
YOU CAN GO ANYWHERE -- ANYWHERE
THAT YOU WANT.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
AAH!
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S COMING.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
OKAY.
WHAT'S UP WITH THE MOON?
[ GASPS ]
[ SHUDDERS ]
NO WAY.
NO WAY. IS THAT...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ISN'T IT AWESOME?
THAT'SAINCRAD -- THE FLOATING
CASTLE.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
HOW?
I MEAN, WHAT'S IT DOING HERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M GONNA BEAT IT.
I'M GONNA GO FLOOR BY FLOOR, ALL
HUNDRED OF THEM, AND THIS TIME,
I'M GONNA CONQUER IT.
LEAFA, I WENT AHEAD AND RESET
ALL MY STATS SO I'M STARTING
FROM SCRATCH AGAIN.
DO YOU WANT TO HELP ME BEAT IT?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
MM-HMM. I WILL.
I'LL GO ANYWHERE...WITH YOU.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HEY, KIRITO!
YOU'RE LATE, MAN.
WE'RE GONNA LEAVE YOU BEHIND!
&gt;&gt; Agil: SEE YOU THERE!
&gt;&gt; COME ON!
&gt;&gt; HURRY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: COME ON, KIRITO,
LEAFA.
LET'S GO.
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; HURRY, DADDY.
EVERYONE'S WAITING.
[ NO AUDIO ]
OKAY, LET'S GO!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]