Summer's in full swing!
We're talking puffy white clouds, cicada's buzzing,
the whole bit.
Nice!
Dressed to impress! That's how it's done!
This doesn't make me look dorky?
No, not at all.
Uh, excuse me.
Eh?
Well, do I look adorable or what?
You definitely look something.
Uh-huh. Say it. I have a glow.
Or a bun in the oven.
Same thing. Wow, just imagine.
The outfit might get people
thinking that you and me are...
Oh dear. Careful.
With a butt like that you've got to pay attention
to your center of gravity.
Might help a little if you didn't shove me!
Alrighty. Train's about to leave. So, yeah.
With Kei and Yoshida doing their thing abroad
over the summer break,
I thought it'd fun to take Ringo along
with Minori and me for a visit back home to the boonies.
But, oh man, was there ever a perfect storm brewing.
Would I live to tell the tale?
Your guess is as good as mine!
The Nagaragawa Railway.
Naga Rail for short.
Run these days by a third-tier public transit company,
it picks up where the old Etsumi South Line left off.
Okay, this rice is perfect for mealtime
on the rails.
Mm. Very tasty.
So, uh, exactly how far out is your hometown?
Oh, it's in the middle of nowhere.
But, Minori's family's nice.
Give Ringo the rundown on your three sisters.
Tsukasa's the oldest, then I came along.
The two youngest are twins: Takumi and Akin.
Cool.
Ah, Tsukasa. Hey, uh...
So she moved back home not that long ago, right?
What was she doing?
Ahh... Little of this, little of that.
You know, whatever keeps a gal like her busy.
Heh. Guess the old crowd
didn't nickname her "The General" for nothing.
It's weird she came back, though.
Figured she'd still be out there blazing a trail.
Uh-oh. Stay still!
So... Some special reason he's along for the ride?
Gee. I don't know, uh...
Little fella gets super lonely when you're not around,
and he's got kind of a sixth sense for where you are.
Whatever. You're keeping tabs on him, though.
Far as this trip's concerned, he's your mess.
Mm-hmm! In you go, love.
Make yourself at home.
Uh. Okay. What the...?
I made a special pouch for him in there.
Awkward. Now you really do look preggers.
Attention passengers,
if you peek out your window right now,
you'll see we're passing over
the First Nagara River Bridge.
So cool.
Check it out, they're waving! Ha!
C'mon, you too.
Uh, okay.
Hello!
Hey, Kousaku?
Huh?
You know... I've been on my share of trains and stuff,
but this one's probably my favorite.
Next stop, Aioi.
Thank you for choosing Nagaragawa Railway.
We hope you have a pleasant day.
Where's the attendant?
Oh there isn't one. The station's unmanned.
Bubba! Sissy!
Welcome back!
Taku and Aki!
Someone's been eating their vegetables!
Hey! How come Sissy's got such a big tummy?
Now, now. Don't poke.
She's carrying precious cargo in there,
not just her usual roll of fat.
Ha! Well, well!
You just couldn't stay away, huh?
Oh, hey Tsukasa!
Whoa! We're getting a ride from The General herself?
You eat a watermelon on the train?
Wait...
Am I crazy or is the middle
child sporting a motherly glow?
Knock if off, Sis. Jeepers.
You're going to embarrass me in front of everybody.
Don't be so self-conscious.
You look absolutely fabulous.
Thank you.
You've filled out a bit, too, Kousaku.
How're things?
Finer than frog hair split four ways.
Frog hair?
Oh, country-folk jibber-jab.
Welcome to the sticks, Ringo.
This is how we do. No standing on ceremony.
You'll be just fine.
How do you know my name?
Ha! We're all up in everybody's business here.
Right. Load up and climb in!
Time's wasting, fam's waiting.
Heh. Tiger gets shotgun.
Seriously?
Aunt Hisako, Uncle Kiichi. What are we doing here again?
Exchanging engagement gifts!
Oh, yeah? Who's engaged?
Good one. You and Minori, my boy!
Sister. I thank you. My heart...
Miiinoooriii!!
Sorry, the jig is up! I get why you dragged me out here!
Wakadana has a sixth sense, huh?
Oh-ho, motherly glow, eh?
You are absolutely the worst kind of person!
Darling, please, save it for later!
No time like the present for truth!
Minori!
What in heaven's name is that?!
It's a wallaby from school!
But she?
Young lady! What is the meaning of this?
I caved under the pressure
to give you grandchildren, okay?!
I see what you did there.
Let me give you some sisterly advice, Hondo.
Next time you want us all to think you're expecting
a visit from the stork, make sure the proud papa-to-be
is in on the scam. You know this is pathetic, right?
Yeah...
Well, what I'd like to know is how you
all fell for it in the first place!
I mean, how could you possibly think
me and her were going to be parents?
How gullible can you be?
Sorry! Never mind about that!
The thing is, though... What's the big rush?
Kousaku.
Ma'am?
Here's the deal.
I'm getting a non-profit off the ground.
This here town needs it.
Uh... Oh yeah?
We're calling it "Turn A!"
Do what now?
In city talk, coming back to the country
is a U-turn, or, sometimes, an I-turn.
But I'm thinking alpha.
A-turn is sort of clumsy in practice, though.
So I "turned it around" and there you have it:
coming back to your roots!
See, "A" also stands for Aioi!
Deal is, the town's about to
put on it's first full-fledged
Turn-A extravaganza.
I banked on you two getting hitched
being the big draw that brings in the crowds.
Huh? How so?
A mixer?
You bet! Two hundred upwardly mobile singles
mingling together over country-fried hors d'oeuvres
right here in Aioi!
Hm!
And you two were gonna be the big focus.
Young couple in love makes good
-our own farm-raised success!
Couple?
In love?
Whoaaa!
You first locked eyes in Aioi.
married in Aioi, live in Aioi, work and play in Aioi,
and are about to be one baby
into rearing a family in Aioi.
You two'll be the ideal PR centerpiece
for what this mixer's meant to accomplish!
I've got morning sickness.
Here's the plan, chief:
you're going to get my sister in a family way, pronto.
You're practically engaged as it
is, so what the hey, right?
Yes!
Come on, boy! Think of the village!
The village!
This is crazy! How am I supposed to just... ?
Look, kid: we borrowed a lot
of dough to make this happen.
If the mixer gets called off,
we're a million in the hole.
In other words, I'd be happy to
help my community any way I can.
Yeah! Let's get this party started!
Yeah!
We'll seal your engagement
at the community center!
Young couple!
Young love!
This is gonna be great!
We're going to be so friggin' happy!
Man, what a crazy day.
Um, where's Ringo?
I put her up in the guestroom. Poor dear was exhausted.
I'll bet.
Guess today was a pretty big shock to her system, too.
Don't worry, though. I've got a bed ready for you.
Yeah?
Takes you back, doesn't it? In you go!
Crap!
Sweet dreams, future son-in-law!
You locked the door? What if I have to pee?
Memory lane, huh?
Remember back in the day how you'd always wet the bed?
Gee, thanks.
Damn. Should've known. Towns like this...
There's nothing they won't do to counteract
the declining birthrate!
I'm essentially breeding stock to these people!
So, uh, you know...
I have kind of a suggestion
to make if you're open to it.
It's actually a swell idea.
Oh, yeah? Go on.
Well, uh... If you... I mean, you and me...
Made, you know, like a baby...
My folks would get off our back.
So...?
What?
What?!
What?!!
Just think about it for a sec.
They're really only rushing us
'cause there ain't no babies around.
If we got started making them one,
they'd change their tune in a heartbeat, right?
Yeah! Not the problem! Forget it!
That is not a viable solution, period!
Aw, c'mon, Kousaku! You like kids, don't you?
Yeah? Don't be a grump.
Look at you.
You'd be a great dad and you know it.
In fact, our kid'd probably be your spitting image.
Wouldn't that be super-duper cute?
You're... You're serious.
Of course I am.
Hey, remember when your parents first brought you over?
We were little.
I can see it like it was yesterday.
There you were, hiding behind your mom and dad,
not looking up at me even once.
What did you expect? I was scared.
We'd just up and moved on a whim.
I had no idea what was going on.
I know. It's just...
The expression on your face always stuck with me,
kind of like you were halfway
between tears and a tantrum.
See, I knew right then that I
could never leave you alone.
You need me.
Or someone, at least. Might as well be me.
Thing is, I want to be there for you.
Look... We... I...
Bubba!
Sissy!
We want to sleep here with you tonight!
Uh... Sure! Why not? Eh?
Yeah! Cool beans! We'll have a slumber party.
Just like the old days.
Yay!
Good morning.
Good morning, my darling Koutan!
Back after while, Tsukasa and me
are making arrangements for the wedding.
Your Loving Wife.
The-They're really going to go
through with this, aren't they?!
Morning.
Oh, hey! Morning!
Did, uh, you sleep okay?
Where's the gang?
Huh? Oh. The day starts super early on a farm.
Hey, uh.
What would you say to me giving you a little tour?
Cool.
Everybody's so hard at work already.
If there's one hard and fast rule in the country,
it's get your work in while the weather's nice.
Uncle Kiichi lives by that.
He's always the first one up.
Also the last guy to call it a day.
One of his prize-winning tomatoes. Here, try a bite.
Good, right?
He uses a special technique and everything.
Too bad he won't be able to pass
it down to future generations.
Wait. He can't?
Not a lot of people left in rural places
like this. The old ways have been on the down swing
for a while now.
I wonder...
What do you think came first, the chicken or the egg?
Are people leaving 'cause farming's not popular,
or is it the other way around?
Maybe farming's losing its appeal for people
'cause so many farmers are calling it quits?
If there was a way to make it all attractive again,
people would start moving back
out to the country in droves.
Make farming attractive.
That must be what Tsukasa is trying to get at.
Can't really blame the girl for trying, huh?
You know Kiichi's oldest daughter?
Well, just like that, she's back,
stirring up all manner of heaven only knows what.
That's the union chief and the mayor.
Oh, I heard.
"The General" thinks she can
bring in a lot of new blood.
Like they won't pick up and
leave at first sign of trouble.
Remember that family came up from the city
once upon a time? Hata, I think the name was?
It'll be that all over again.
What's the verdict on Kiichi's girl?
She abandoned ship once.
Stands to reason she'll do it again.
Guarantee you her enthusiasm won't survive the month.
Well now, if you ask me, that's being right generous.
What did they mean "it'll be that all over again?"
Kousaku, I want to see your house.
I'm talking to you!
There's nothing to see.
It's there, it's just not a house anymore.
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
Can we not go there, please?
It's not a pleasant story.
Jerk.
Uh?
Huh?
So Minori would know what you were talking about.
But you won't "go there" with me?
It's totally unfair.
My parents got the farming bug when I was little.
Thought it was the end all be all.
One day they just up and moved here.
Hauled stakes from the big city with me in tow.
Only took them a season to figure out
they'd bitten off more than they could chew.
What happened?
In so many words...
The tomato crop they were banking on failed.
Put 'em in so much,
debt they couldn't get out from under it.
To make ends meet, Mom took a part-time job.
Dad was always off somewhere away from home
trying to scare up capital.
That was the big irony.
The more they tried to salvage the farm,
the less they could be here to tend the damn thing.
When Mom buckled under the stress
and had a nervous breakdown,
Dad travelled further and further
away from home to try to scrounge up money
for medical bills.
Eventually I saw him less and less, until...
Till what?
Till the morning Mom's poor old heart
finally gave out.
That's when Dad said to hell with the farm
and left Aioi for good. Haven't seen him since.
Yeah, so... In come Uncle Kiichi and Auntie Hisako,
who took me under their wing an raised me as their own.
And Minori?
Huh?
Wha-What is she to you?
Well. I...
Bubba! Whatcha doin'?
Showing my pal Ringo here the sights.
This is the best view in the village.
I want to show you how many exercise stamps
I've collected!
Me, too! Look, I have a whole big bunch!
Good morning.
Hm? Hey.
Come on, where are your manners, guys?
Ah... Are you a princess?
'Cause you... you look like one.
Yeah.
Seriously?
How come?
Why's a real, live princess
staying in a house like ours?
Oh, uh...
It's summer vacation.
Princesses get summer vacation, too?
Mm-hmm.
Wait, but... What country are you princess of?
It's, uh... It's called Yukatania.
Where's that?
Well it's kind of in the heart of your awesome
grown-up friend here.
Do you have, like, a job there and stuff?
I'm responsible for all the cuteness.
Can I be the person who carries the back of your dress
when you walk?
Me, too! Me, too!
I can't think of anybody better.
Yay!
Your Highness! You have to see something really cool!
Watermelon!
Whoa, hold up.
The little ones have sure taken a shine to our guest.
She's a princess!
We're her retainers!
Is that a fact now?
Hey, uh, when you're done with that,
I'd love to show you a sending off.
A what?
So where are we going?
To the river.
What's there to do down there?
What's there to do? Float paper lanterns downstream!
It's a "Sending Off" ceremony!
Let me! I want to put one in by myself!
Me, too!
Now, now kiddos.
Careful where you step. Don't fall in.
I've got this, thank you.
Now, the important part: Say goodbye to your ancestors.
They gotta hear you.
Safe journey!
Wow...
We can move to a better spot if you want.
I know a place with a way better view.
Gorgeous!
Cool. Thought you'd like it.
Do the lanterns make it to the ocean?
Nah. There's a big net just after the bend.
They'll collect them all tomorrow morning.
Sorry. Kind of takes the magic out of it, huh?
No, not really.
That's country life.
The real magic is in seeing it from far away.
Close up, sometimes it's easy to feel like an outsider,
hard to know where you fit in.
Sorry I got all weird with you about my folks...
I should've told you before.
I wonder.
It's tough here.
And I know farming's not for everyone.
But... so what?
Give me this view and the clean air any day.
The water's fresh, the mountains are
close, and the food is delicious.
Plus any village that raised you must be wonderful.
Now that summer's here our hearts indulge the weather
Quietly we sit together,
Our hands entwined, the stars up above;
Oh, please let me be selfish, my love.
Let me see desire move you
When you glimpse me in my brand new
bathing suit, pool side
Instead of this uniform... why hide?
This moment's for you and me,
So before we say goodbye
Let me lay bare what I need courage to share
With a special guy...
Timidly on my cell phone...
Just so you know, that was me.
Not Yuka Kusakabe... But the real me.
Everybody's No-Rin.