[bell ringing]
[HIRATA] First, let's go over
what we already know.
The school provided two tents
that each sleep eight,
so we have some shelter, two
flashlights, one box of matches,
backpacks, and amenities
for everyone in class.
And sunscreen for
anyone who wants it.
A whole week with
only the basics?
A survival test on a
desert island, for real?
Just proceed as we discussed.
Right.
And get over yourself, too.
We both know that ever since
the rumor went around
that you tried get into
the student council
and got rejected,
Sakayanagi's faction has
achieved dominance.
This is a great opportunity
for the both of us.
[HIRATA] So, we have
to find our own food.
A test of survival, outdoors.
Ending at noon,
one week from now.
[YAMAUCHI] But remember
what the teachers told us?
We can still go swimming,
have barbecues,
and all that other fun stuff.
[HIRATA] No, we can only
do that if we spend
the 300 S-points they gave us,
which would be a waste,
considering what we could buy.
Food, drinking water,
tools to cook with.
So you aren't gonna
buy those things?
Look, if we have any S-points
left at the end of the test,
then they'll be added to our
class's total point score.
If we can tough it out
for the whole week,
we'll get 30,000 a month!
Thirty thousand, guys!
[KARUIZAWA]
What's that?
[HIRATA] A list of things
we could lose points for.
Illness and serious injuries.
Pollution of the
surrounding environment.
Absence at morning
and evening roll calls.
Violence against, or stealing
from other classes.
[KARUIZAWA] But we can gain
more points, can't we?
[HIRATA]
Yes.
There are certain "spots"
around the island
we can claim as our own
to get bonus points.
"Freedom to choose,"
is the theme of this test.
Don't ya think?
Sure seems that way.
If we do this right,
we could close the gap
between us and
the other classes.
This thing is so restrictive.
But there's a penalty
for removing the ID watches.
I don't think it's wise
to risk it, y'know?
There are special sensors
and GPS devices
hidden in these things.
So they can find us quickly
if there's an emergency, I bet.
Hey, Hirata, don't
you think we should
be able to spend some of
our points, within reason?
[HIRATA]
Hm...
No!
We should refrain from using
points for as long as we can.
Don't you realize how
difficult that's going to be?
[SHINO] Are we supposed to
go to the bathroom in this?
[SATO]
I'll, like, die!
[HIRATA]
A basic toilet?
I'd prefer to tough it out.
That won't be a problem
for me, personally,
but I don't think some
of the other girls can.
[AYANOKOJI]
A basic toilet.
You use a hyper-absorbent
polymer sheet to solidify waste.
Each one can be used many times.
I think.
That might be hard on the women.
[SUZUNE]
That's very likely.
Come on, we can just tough
it out and use this toilet!
You're not listening!
I'm saying that
some of the girls
might not be willing
or able to do that!
We can buy a regular
toilet with points.
See, it says so right
here on the list.
[KARUIZAWA]
That's perfect!
[HASE]
Yeah!
[SATO]
We totally have to!
[SHINO]
Let's buy it right now!
[YUKIMURA]
You can't just decide that.
We shouldn't be able to
spend collective points
without a majority vote.
[YAMAUCHI]
A majority vote!
That's a great idea, Yukimura!
[IKE] This is our chance to
score some major class points!
We can do without
the fancy toilet.
What the--?
Women are emotional creatures
who become irrational
when they get triggered,
so you shouldn't
indulge them, Hirata.
Say that again, jerk!
Hey, relax. Do you wanna
prove the guy right?
[SATO] Think about it from
our perspective for a minute!
[SHINO] I'm not gonna go
to the bathroom where...
This doesn't bode well.
This test is shaping up to be
much more complicated
than I thought.
I don't know if we can cut it.
[AYANOKOJI] Ike, Yamauchi,
and Sudo went on an expedition.
They're looking for
a place to camp,
and any of those "spots"
that were mentioned.
[AYANOKOJI]
You're not having a good time?
[SUZUNE]
This isn't exactly my forte.
On many levels:
for one, roughing it.
And, two, having to
be around people.
[AYANOKOJI]
I can understand that.
Even though it pains me,
I guess I've got to admit
the hypothesis you posed
to me once upon a time
was eerily accurate.
This school will
test us on a metric
involving more than academics.
That's what you said to me.
Yeah.
Ike and Sudo volunteered
to go explore the forest
in search of a camp site.
I wouldn't even know
how to handle that.
Are you going to be okay,
despite everything?
[SUZUNE]
Doesn't matter.
If Classes A and B are
searching for these "spots,"
we would be wise to do
the same. Don't you think?
[AYANOKOJI] Aiming for a higher
class is harder than I thought.
[SUZUNE] Well, yeah, but don't
you want what it offers?
[AYANOKOJI]
What do ya mean?
[SUZUNE]
The guarantee you'll get the job
or university you want.
I assumed that anyone
who came to this school
did so because they wanted that.
[HIRATA]
A class of more than 20 people.
An unfamiliar basic toilet.
You really think there
won't be any trouble?
We'll just have to
make the best of it all.
Sharing a primitive toilet
is guaranteed to
bring up problems.
I think spending
points in moderation
is the best course of action.
Reckless self-deprivation
and uncertainty
will stress everyone out,
which increases conflict.
Not to mention
the hygiene issues.
The girls need peace of mind.
It will make them more likely
to succeed in the exam. Y'know?
Yeah, you're right.
[AYANOKOJI] He would never
argue against solid logic.
I think it's time for us
to start searching the forest
for a good place to
set up our base camp.
I agree.
[HIRATA] Where we decide
to camp will definitely
affect how and when we have
to spend our points this week.
Are there any volunteers
to help me search?
Oh, right here!
I'd be honored to help,
if you'll have me!
Aren't you going
to join the fun?
That's the last
thing I wanna do.
And you?
Volunteering to help
those guys look?
I've gotta say,
I'm quite surprised.
Not taking any kind of role
makes you stand out
from the group.
[HIRATA] Thanks a lot,
Sakura. That makes nine.
Let's proceed in teams of three.
[KOENJI laughs]
Ah, yes, I am so beautiful.
And melding with the exquisite
environment around me
only enhances my stellar looks.
I'm the pinnacle of beauty.
[AYANOKOJI] Excellent athletic
ability, and no sign
of reticence about
the outdoors, either.
What's his story?
[SAKURA] Ayanokoji.
Walking in this jungle.
It's pretty difficult, isn't it?
[AYANOKOJI] Yes, and it's
incredibly hot, on top of that.
Hey, are you gonna be okay?
I'm fine. Don't worry!
Well, that's good.
Let's pick up the pace.
Uh, yeah.
Koenji sure is amazing, right?
[AYANOKOJI] Yeah, and it's
not just his athleticism.
He's insanely confident
all the time, too.
Koenji, wait! Don't go
too fast, please.
[KOENJI]
No need to worry.
A little jungle like this
is no match for me!
What's that supposed to mean?
As long as the sun
is still shining,
there's very little
chance of getting lost
while wandering around
a forest like this one.
It's intriguing.
That's why I'm having
the time of my life!
[AYANOKOJI]
He keeps speeding up.
Koenji.
[SAKURA pants] Don't worry
about me, really. I'm okay.
[AYANOKOJI sighs]
Huh, lost sight of him again.
I wonder how fast that guy was
flying through the tree tops.
It's crazy.
Do you think this
is one of the paths?
[AYANOKOJI]
It certainly looks like it.
[SAKURA gasps]
Wow.
I wonder if that cave is one
of the spots they mentioned.
Most likely.
[CHABASHIRA]
There are multiple "spots"
scattered throughout the island.
Each time you gain possession
of one of these spots.
You will earn a single
bonus point for your class.
However, you can't
spend any bonus points
during the test period.
They'll be added
to your class total
after the test has finished.
Each declaration of
possession of a spot
lasts for eight hours.
Only the class leader
has the authority
to declare possession.
You said class leader?
That's right.
This key card is used to
take possession of a spot.
Only the leader gets one.
Also, you can't change leaders
without having a legitimate
reason to do so.
In addition to that,
on the last day of the test,
when we take roll,
for each class leader you are
able to correctly identify,
your class will be
allotted a whopping
50 bonus points,
right then and there.
[SAKURA]
Fifty bonus points?
[KEN] So if we guess all
three classes' leaders,
we'll get 150 bonus points?
However, for each
incorrect guess,
you'll lose 50 points.
This is a high-risk,
high-return game.
It's in your best interest
to try to find out
who the other class leaders are,
but also to make an effort
to conceal your
leader's identity.
[AYANOKOJI]
Spots are important, I guess,
but moving too hastily
to secure them
could result in your
leader being revealed.
[gasps]
[YAHIKO] We sure got lucky
this time, right, Katsuragi?
Securing a spot like this
so early in the week?
Lucky?
I've had my eye on it
since before we landed.
Finding it was expected.
Another thing. Be careful
what you say and do.
Oh, right.
We don't know who might be
eavesdropping out here.
So, take extra care not to
accidentally reveal anything.
As leader, it's
my responsibility
to manage our class.
Yeah. I'll be careful.
Before we docked today,
the ship took a slow lap around
the island at a distance.
That was a hint.
[YAHIKO]
How was that a hint?
Even from that far away,
I could see there were paths
cut through the jungle.
Then I knew I just had to
find the shortest routes.
You could tell what the school
was trying to do just from
that? Brilliant, as usual.
You know what?
Sakayanagi's got nothin'
on you, dude.
Hold on for a second.
Something's odd.
What is it, Katsuragi?
Um. What's up?
Nothing. Let's get moving.
We shouldn't stay here too long.
[AYANOKOJI]
That was a close call.
Sorry, Sakura.
Sakura?
[SAKURA groans]
[AYANOKOJI]
Are you okay?
I-I-I-I-I'm--
I'm okay.
[AYANOKOJI]
Those two guys.
They're in Class A, right?
[SAKURA]
Uh, yeah.
Hey, Ayanokoji?
Does that conversation
mean that bald guy
is Class A's leader?
So, we just learned an
invaluable secret, didn't we?
[AYANOKOJI]
Yeah.
I'll report it to Hirata later,
when we get back.
He ditched you?
Well, that's Koenji.
Yeah.
And it's not like
I have the ability
to control a person like that.
As I'm sure you're aware.
[HIRATA] Good news, everybody!
Ike and the others.
They found a great spot
at the head of a river!
Why don't we go
meet up with them!
This is it!
Don't you think it's
the best spot ever?
[KARUIZAWA gasps]
The water's so clear!
--[HIRATA] Thanks, you guys.
--[KIKYO] It's beautiful!
[SHINO] It's a lot
cooler than I thought!
[HIDEO]
You think we can drink it?
I know!
There it is.
Useless to me.
Only the class leader can take
possession of a spot. Huh.
So, assuming we wanna set up
our base camp right here,
we had better discuss
taking possession of it.
[IKE]
We should, shouldn't we?
If we do, we get unlimited
access to the river,
and we'll also get points
every eight hours!
Although, it isn't quite
as simple as that.
The leader's gotta renew
possession to get those points.
That's right. If another
class sees them do it...
Can't we just, like,
surround them while
they renew it?
Good idea! What do
you guys think?
[MATSUSHITA]
Yeah, that sounds like a plan!
[HASE] We have enough
people to block them.
[STUDENT 9A]
Yeah, form a ring around them!
Last question then.
Who'll be our fearless leader?
[MITA]
Let's see.
I think Hirata should
be our leader!
[STUDENT 9A]
Hirata's the natural choice.
Hey, guys. I have
something to say!
I've really been thinking
about this a lot.
People like Hirata and
Karuizawa stand out,
even if they don't intend to.
And the person we
elect as our leader
should be someone who
flies under the radar,
but they need to be
responsible, too, right?
Only one of our classmates
fits both requirements.
And, that person's Horikita.
[KIKYO]
What do you think?
I'm in favor!
Horikita, if you'll accept the
role, I'd like you to have it.
What do ya say?
If she won't,
I'd be happy to be
the class leader.
[SUZUNE] Ugh, fine, then.
I accept the position.
[AYANOKOJI]
Ouch.
Okay!
That addresses the issue
of bathing and drinking water
for the whole week. Huh?
Yeah. I guess.
It looks drinkable, anyway.
[KARUIZAWA] Are you sure
this is safe to drink?
I mean, it is a river.
[SHINO]
What if there's bacteria?
[HASE]
Can you tell?
[IKE]
What's the matter with you guys?
We found a freakin' river!
There's no way we're
not going to use it!
[HIRATA]
We do have some time.
There's no need to make
a hasty decision about it.
[KARUIZAWA]
Uh, yeah!
[SHINO]
He's right.
[HASE]
Kinda risky, don't you think?
Ike.
You have experience
in the great outdoors?
Yeah, I do. My family
loves camping
and we used to go every
weekend when I was little.
I have no problem with
drinking river water.
[IKE] Sometimes you can tell
if a spring is drinkable
just by looking at it.
Ayanokoji. Could I
talk to you for a sec?
Before it gets dark,
I'd like you to gather
some branches for us
to use as firewood tonight.
Yeah, okay. I'll get
on that right now.
Wait! It's too dangerous
for you to go on your own!
[AYANOKOJI]
I'll find someone to help me.
Great!
[SUZUNE] Despite being
the big man in Class D.
He still has to rely
on you to help him.
Pathetic, isn't it?
[AYANOKOJI] It wouldn't
kill you to help out a little,
too, fearless leader.
We both know there's nothing
that I can help with.
I'm useless right now.
But if an enemy or other
objective turns up,
I'll be happy to
offer my thoughts.
[AYANOKOJI]
Hey. I'm gathering branches.
You could help.
[YAMAUCHI]
Hm?
Listen, Ayanokoji.
I think I'm gonna
go after Sakura.
Let's face it: Kushida is
way out of my league.
Yes, and?
But a girl like Sakura--
if I can convince her that
I'm a sensitive, caring guy,
I just know she'll fall for me.
[AYANOKOJI] Is that why you
decided to tag along and help?
Hey, Sakura, are you tired?
Do you need help carrying those?
Must be such hard
work for a girl,
and you might hurt
your sweet little self.
Uh. It's fine I'm okay.
Hey, what's the matter?
Wha--? What the heck
is your problem?
Oh. Nevermind, it's fine.
[YAMAUCHI]
Hey, everything all right?
Just leave me alone.
I don't need help.
You must be in a lot
of pain, though.
You're Ibuki from
Class C, right?
Did your classmates
do something to you?
[YAMAUCHI] The three of us
are students from Class D.
You can come back to our base
camp with us, if you want.
[SAKURA]
Yeah.
Didn't you hear me?
I don't need your help.
And I'm in Class C,
which means I'm your enemy.
We can't leave you
out here all alone!
Right?
[SAKURA]
Mm-hm.
We'll stay right here with you.
When you can walk,
we'll let you go.
[IBUKI]
How stupid can you be?
You shouldn't trust me.
No one in my class would
dream of doing this.
[IKE] You can't start a fire
with branches alone, see?
But if you build it like this,
I think it'll light up nicely.
And there we go!
Experienced camper, huh?
You sure know your stuff!
That's the most
basic of the basics!
Anybody can do it
once they know!
That's pretty cool!
[KIKYO]
Hey, we're back!
[KIKYO] Do you think...
that this one's edible?
I don't know about that.
They could be blueberries!
Hey, those are bog bilberries!
Are you the one who found
those, Kikyo? Awesome!
[KIKYO]
So, Kanji.
Do you know what those
brown things are?
I'm pretty sure
that those are figs!
They're deliciously sweet,
like nothing else.
Man, this brings me back!
[KARUIZAWA]
Oh, really?
Ike, you know all
about this stuff.
It's so reassuring.
[AYANOKOJI]
Check out the fire.
Ike started that, too.
[KIKYO]
Kanji, you really are amazing!
[SATO]
I agree!
[HIDEO] He did such a great
job starting the fire...
[YAMAUCHI]
He found the river, too!
[INO] I'm grateful
that we have someone
so experienced in our class!
Hey, Karuizawa.
Sorry about before.
Wha--? Where did that come from?
I just remembered something.
The first time my
family went camping,
the bathroom stuff was hard.
I complained to my
parents the whole time.
It must be even harder
for girls, right?
[AYANOKOJI]
Ike can admit he was wrong
without getting worked up?
That's impressive.
He's a better man than me.
[KARUIZAWA]
I'm sorry, too, Ike.
We've gotta push our
limits now and then
if we wanna have any points
left at the end of all this.
[HIRATA] Hey, you guys.
Can I say something?
I think it's important for us
to trust and rely on each other
as much as possible until
the end of this special test.
So, here's my idea.
Of the 300 S-points,
let's aim to have 120
of 'em left by the end.
What do you guys say?
Is that doable?
You mean you want
to spend 180 points?
[HIRATA] If we didn't have Ike,
and had to buy it all,
food and water.
That's every meal for
every single one of us
for seven days.
The most efficient way
would be the rations
and mineral water set.
It's ten S-points each for
one meal for all of us.
What do you think?
He's pretty spot-on.
I've been turning
those exact numbers
over in my mind all day.
Did you share that
bit with Hirata?
[SUZUNE] Of course not.
You're joking, right?
See?
A hundred and twenty S-points
is more than you might think.
After all, remember the
test results from earlier?
Think of those numbers.
Class A's total points changed
by how much again? Uh, I forgot.
It was 94 points.
And that's if we
do the very least.
For every day that we can find
food and water on our own...
...we'll be able to save
20 S-points on those days!
[HIRATA] If we can make it
the whole week without
buying drinking water,
we can save
50 points that way alone.
Oh, that's good.
[IKE]
Let's give it a shot, Hirata!
[HIRATA]
All right, then, sounds good.
Let's all do our best!
[AYANOKOJI]
Sorry about this.
Just a little bit longer.
See. Those guys by the fire.
They're discussing what
to do with you now.
[IBUKI] You shouldn't
go out of your way.
It's just a matter of time
before they cast me out.
I wouldn't be so sure.
We have a few trusting types.
[KIKYO]
Your name's Ibuki, right?
Here. You should eat.
[IBUKI] You're all idiots.
Every single one of you.
Oh, just eat. What harm
is there in that?
We can have a talk later, too,
if you're feeling up to it.
[KEN]
Damn that stupid punk! Koenji!
[STUDENT 9B]
How could he do this?
[STUDENT 9]
He's a selfish jerk!
[STUDENT 9D] How will that
affect our points...
[KIKYO]
What happened?
Koenji said he was feeling sick
and went back to the boat!
[gasps]
According to the
rules of the test,
his illness alone will
cost Class D 30 S-points.
Koenji will be out of the game,
and he's required to stay
on the ship and recover.
He can't come back.
[KIKYO]
Oh, no!
[laughs]
[KOENJI]
The moon is beautiful!