Hello, lovely members of Class One-B.
Let's all try to have a wonderful day, shall we?
Ew! Teacher, you reek of alcohol!
Yeah, I had a bit too much last night.
And now, it's time to announce each class's point totals
for the mont--
As for your personal points,
those will be distributed to you all tomorrow.
Check it out! Our class points went up!
That's amazing!
Do you think it's because we just aced the midterms?
I bet your study group brought everyone's scores up!
No way. It's because you've all worked so hard!
I love you, Ichinose!
Whoa, Chihiro! Calm down!
So do I!
Hey, get off me!
You're my hero!
Fine.
I'm grateful. I adore being here in Class One-B.
'Cause it's the same class Ichinose's in.
I gotta say.
I'm also grateful to be in Class One-B.
Because even though our homeroom teacher
may be a little eccentric,
my classmates are all such wonderful people.
And, that's why I'll do my best.
I want us all to be in Class
A, and we'll make it together!
Uh?
You getting in? Or just standing there?
Getting in. Why would I do anything else?
Good morning! How are you doing today?
Looks like you've got some wicked bedhead going on.
Bedhead is back in style these days, you know.
You're hilarious.
You can always crack me up.
Understand? If you betray me, you'll pay.
Well, then, maybe I'll stop
worrying about my bedhead, too!
I have to live in the same dorm as her
for the next three years.
What's going on here?
Seeing you and Kushida standing together is... strange.
She was waiting for me outside my door.
Ah... I was really hoping she would let me
walk to class with her today.
Good morning, Kushida!
Uh? Ichinose!
Whoa, Kushida, is that your new boyfriend?
No, he's just a friend.
I wonder how she really feels about me.
Oh, by the way.
So, in Class D. Did you get your points yet?
There's been something of an issue.
The provision of points to the
first-years has been delayed.
What? Are you kidding me?
Well, are we going to be compensated in some way
for the school's screw up?
Regrettably, there's nothing I can do about that.
Rest assured that when it's fixed,
then you will all get your points.
Assuming you still have any by then, of course.
Uh, hey there.
I'm sorry about this.
That's a strange greeting. What's up?
It's just that...
Well, I have to say this.
I'm pretty sure...
...someone is about to ask me out!
Like, right now!
Huh? Wait, I'm confused.
Wouldn't it be better if I wasn't here?
Well, normally, but I don't know a thing about dating!
Someone left this in my locker yesterday.
And the feeling is not mutual.
And I have no idea how to let them down easy.
Without hurting them, you know?
So, I was wondering if you might help me out
by pretending to be my boyfriend for a sec.
She seriously thinks that's going to work?
I'm begging you!
I think it would be better to just be honest with them
and hash it out. That's my advice.
I can't!
Ichinose.
Who is this person?
Uh! Look, I'm really sorry.
I know you don't know this guy,
I wasn't trying to be rude or anything.
Um, this is Ayanokoji, and he's in Class One-D.
Is he your boyfriend?
You could have told me.
Well, Ayanokoji and I...
He and I are--
Just friends, don't worry.
Ichinose. It's hard to confess your feelings.
It makes you so open and vulnerable.
You spend every day in agony, but you still can't do it.
That's a painful place to be.
The words, "I love you," stick in your throat,
and no matter how hard you try, you can't force them out.
She was brave, so she deserves an honest answer.
Do you think you can give her that much, at least?
But, it's also not my place to get involved.
Hello, again. Looks like you talked it out.
Yeah.
It's funny.
All I could think about was
how to get out of hurting her feelings.
But the truth of it is, I was just running away.
We've reached an agreement.
We're going to try to go back to normal tomorrow.
Here's hoping.
You'll both have to commit to it.
Yeah.
Anyway, sorry.
I put you in an awkward position.
No worries.
I don't mind some weirdness now and then.
I guess this means I owe you one, doesn't it?
How intriguing.
I'm telling you, that's not how it went down!
There were three dudes ganging up on me!
Yeah, but still.
I know.
What's all this about?
Hey, Ayanokoji.
I think that something bad might have happened.
Some of the Class C students of the basketball team
have filed a complaint against Sudo.
They say that after practice,
Sudo attacked and injured then without provocation.
They're claiming trauma.
That's a load of crap, it was clear self-defense!
They're jealous that I play first string,
so those jerks decided to pick a damn fight with me!
There's no evidence of that,
but if there were any witnesses
it might be a different story.
Okay! Did any of you happen to see Sudo's fight?
Does anyone know anything about it?
Perhaps everyone would be better off
if you'd been expelled after all.
Ginger Boy.
And people might defend you, if you were pretty.
What?!
Sudo! Calm down.
One week from today,
we will all hold a group discussion.
Class C and the Student Council will attend.
Depending on how things go,
you may be asked to forfeit points,
and Sudo may face other consequences.
♪♪♪
Those poor Class D morons.
Probably throwin' a huge fit.
Listen, Ryuen.
I think somebody might have seen us.
When we were fighting with Sudo,
I got the feeling someone was watching.
Bad boy.
You look like a proper victim now.
Yes. Thank you, sir, you're always right.
Perform your little dance well. Just like we planned.
This is all Sudo's fault.
It totally sucks.
I don't know how I'll survive another month
living on zero points.
Maybe we really would be better
off if he had gotten expelled.
I hear that for sure.
So, do you agree with them?
That Sudo should have gotten expelled for failing?
I have no opinion.
But, what are your thoughts on it?
You know, since you're of the
people who helped him stay here.
At the moment, our class has zero points.
Even if we had been penalized
for someone getting expelled,
we'd be no worse off than we are now.
Yeah, sure, whatever you say.
'Scuse me? I didn't like the way you said that.
You never know when we might be gaining or losing points
with no knowledge of it.
What's that supposed to mean?
We don't know any of the rules.
We might be getting negative
marks that we don't know about.
Demerits for an expulsion might not hit us right now.
They might matter later. We have no idea how it works.
For example, what if one of the requirements for moving up
to Class A is that none of us have been expelled?
Who can say?
You don't know that.
One of the hallmarks of this school
is that they don't share the rulebook with us.
If we wanna reach Class A, we should play the game like
it's life or death, and there are threats at every turn.
Anyway. Sudo is an athlete,
and he's in good standing with the basketball team.
That could wind up being useful in the end.
Hey, guys! Listen up.
I want to be able to trust my classmates.
I think that we should band together to find witnesses
as to what happened with Sudo.
Sure! You can count me in on that.
Well, if you think that's best, Hirata, I'm in.
Yeah, I want to help, too.
If we don't stick up for each other, no one will.
Kushida says it. I do it!
Yeah, me, too!
Hey. You two are going to join us, right?
Do you wanna help us help Sudo?
In light of everything you just said,
you'll certainly be helping them, won't you, Ayanokoji?
You know.
You're the one who wants to
advance to Class A, aren't you?
So, that means you're gonna help us? Thanks so much!
Yeah. Guess I have to.
Horikita, are you in?
You and I should work together.
But if we're trying to find witnesses,
Sudo should stay out of it.
I think that would probably be best, don't you?
I agree.
Involving him would be a conflict of interests.
Yeah, exactly.
Great!
I'm going to share our plan with Sudo, personally.
I'll see you after class, then!
I can't believe we couldn't find any clues or witnesses.
I don't know.
Have you considered the possibility that Sudo is lying?
Well, I sure have.
What about Hirata's group?
No luck. I texted them,
they didn't find anything, either.
Hey, guys!
Ayanokoji! Hey, Kushida!
Oh, it's Ichinose.
Some people in my class told me what's going on.
You guys are holding an investigation, aren't you?
Uh...
Got it. So it's the guys from Class C.
Yeah. Please ask around, and if anyone knows something,
be sure to tell us first.
Definitely. Sorry I can't help you more than that.
I'll tell Class B the whole thing,
and they'll be happy to help you look.
Really? That'd be great--
What are you doing?
This is probably a plot.
Listen. I don't think it's wise to rely on other classes--
Don't worry!
I'm not up to anything weird.
I do owe you one, Ayanokoji, remember?
Ready? Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Hey, Ayanokoji!
Hey. Did you put up this notice?
Yeah! But it was Kanzaki's idea.
We're gathering information through the class's
online message board. Uh.
Look, we already received an email!
Oh, what does it say?
Let's see... A character witness
about one of the guys Sudo fought with, Ishizaki.
They say this guy was a troublemaker in middle school.
Apparently, he was a good fighter, too,
so everyone in school was afraid of him.
That raises some red flags.
The other guys are on the basketball team,
so they're physically fit.
It's unlikely Sudo could beat all of them by himself
without getting hurt.
That's a good point.
Perhaps they initially wanted to beat him up, but instead,
they decided it would be better to frame him
and get him expelled. It fits the story.
You're right, that's plausible.
Anyway, I should pay whoever sent us the information.
Huh? Wait, it's an anonymous tip.
How am I supposed to reward them, then?
I think I know a way.
Uh? Tell me about it, then!
Her guard's totally down.
Will you loan me your student ID?
Of course!
There.
There we go! Thanks!
If we collect any more info,
we'll be sure that you're the first to hear!
'Kay.
How could one person collect so many points?
Hey, everyone.
Oh, welcome back.
Ayanokoji! I decided to get the guys together.
We're having a meeting so we can pool what we've learned.
I gotta say,
I can't believe how empty your room is.
Yeah, he's right.
You don't really have much of anything in here.
You only have the stuff we were provided.
So, Ayanokoji. Are you a minimalist?
No, I'm not. I just don't have extra points to burn.
But all that aside.
How did you guys get into my room?
We had copies of your key made!
How did you manage that?
What's wrong, this is our meeting place, right?
Wait, are you implying
we shouldn't have done that?
Uh, um... I can give mine back.
Well, we aren't going to, we refuse!
Fine. I don't care.
Uh?
Horikita.
Regarding any witnesses--
I'm leaving.
Hey, Horikita! You decided to come after all?
I think it'd be best for everyone
if you'd share what you know.
If you would prefer it, we can stay quiet and just listen.
You've put in a lot of effort with minimal results,
so let me offer some intel.
There was a witness.
And, it was someone close.
You know who it is?
One of our classmates, Sakura, knows something.
What is it that makes you think Sakura saw anything?
When Kushida made the plea in
class for everyone to help out,
pretty much all of our other
classmates turned to face her.
Sakura, on the other hand, stared at her desk.
She was the only one, so...
No good. She's not answering.
Aw...
Dammit! I was starting to think
we were gonna get somewhere with this chick.
But still.
It doesn't even matter if she
is willing to testify or not.
It's not going to make much of a difference.
The question of whether it was self-defense or not
is just a minor detail.
In the big picture, it's nothing.
Haven't you guys figured that out?
--Huh?! --What do mean by that?
Nothing at all.
Goodbye, now.
Sakura, huh.
Honestly, I can't even remember what she looks like.
Mm?
Kushida.
I haven't been able to get it out of my head.
I hate to bug you about it, but do you have any idea
what Horikita was talking about earlier today?
Even if Sudo was acting in self-defense
in the fight, that's not the root of the problem.
It's a bigger issue than just that.
Huh?
Sudo is always talking trash
and being aggressive towards people.
He lashes out over nothing.
The way he acts inevitably makes people resent him.
He comes off as a jerk pretty much all the time.
So, hypothetically, say a murder takes place.
There are two suspects,
one of whom is known to have committed murder in the past.
Now, imagine the other is a moral, law-abiding citizen.
Which one of them would you believe?
I guess I'd believe the law-abiding citizen, honestly.
But the truth is that the so-called "good guy"
could be the murderer.
Where there is so little evidence, people are inclined
to go with what they know from
a person's behavior in the past.
So, you're saying that Sudo
kind of brought this upon himself?
That the way he's acted since school started
led him to this situation?
Yes, and Sudo doesn't get that or think
he's done anything wrong. Look at Horikita.
That's why she won't cooperate with us.
But, I still believe we should make every effort
to help clear Sudo's name.
We wouldn't be good friends if we didn't.
If you think that's the right thing to do,
then follow through with it.
I don't believe that that would be a problem at all.
Right. Not to change the subject,
but once again you seem to know everything
about the way Horikita operates in the world.
I think that might be going a bit far.
Um. Hey, Ayanokoji.
Do you...
Do you think that...
Well, if I... If I were to...
No. Never mind.
As far as stuff with Sakura goes,
I'll approach her alone tomorrow and see what she says.
If we all went together,
I think she'd get intimidated and shut up.
See ya later!
Hey, Sakura!
Um, yes?
There's something that I've
been wanting to talk to you about.
Do you have a moment? It's about this thing with Sudo.
Um. I'm sorry but I can't right now.
There's somewhere I'm supposed to be.
It's only going to take a moment.
This is important!
No, I wasn't there! I really don't know anything!
Oh! Sorry! Are you okay?
Oh, no. It's not turning on.
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to!
Don't be.
This whole thing was my fault!
Wait, come back!
If I get involved,
everyone will find out the truth about me.
No one here can ever know.