- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( sighs )
- Tiamat: PUT SOME LIGHT ON.
- ( clock ticking )
( dings )
- SHE IS RUNNING
QUITE LATE.
- Tiamat:
THINGS DO COME UP.
- INDEED.
OVER THE PAST
FEW WEEKS THOUGH,
"THINGS" HAVE "COME UP"
WITH A SOMEWHAT
ALARMING FREQUENCY.
- ( door opening )
- WELCOME HOME, MILADY.
- Tiamat:
WE'VE BEEN WAITING.
- WELL, I'M BACK.
- INDEED YOU ARE.
LATER AND LATER
IT SEEMS THESE DAYS.
- Tiamat:
UP TO NO GOOD?
- ( sighs )
SORRY I'M LATE.
SOMETHING CAME UP.
- "SOMETHING"?
THAT'S RATHER VAGUE.
- Tiamat:
AS CLEAR AS MUD.
- Alastor:
ALL RIGHT, LADIES,
NO NEED TO INTERROGATE HER
AS SOON AS SHE
COMES IN THE DOOR.
IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
LET HER CLEAN UP
AND CHANGE CLOTHES FIRST.
WE'LL CONTINUE THIS LATER.
DINNER IS SOON, YES?
- YEAH, SO, LATER.
- ( sighs )
- Wilhelmina: THAT IS INDEED
HOW IT PLAYED OUT.
SINCE THAT TIME,
SHE HASN'T SAID A WORD,
NO MATTER HOW MUCH
I PLEAD.
ADDITIONALLY,
THE FLA--
UH... I MEAN...
I SPOKE WITH HER
OTHER GUARDIAN,
AND HE SEEMS TO BE
COVERING FOR HER.
- MR. ALASTOR?
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- ( dings )
- YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT HER.
- ( gasps )
- WELL, OF COURSE.
THAT'S ONLY NATURAL.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE SHANA
TO JUST STOP TALKING TO YOU.
- ( sighs )
- IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
I'VE SPENT QUITE A GOOD DEAL
OF TIME WITH HER THIS YEAR,
AND I WOULD SAY THAT
I UNDERSTAND HER
REASONABLY WELL,
I THINK.
FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN,
SHE ISN'T THE KIND OF GIRL
WHO WOULD HIDE SOMETHING,
NOT FROM SOMEONE
SHE DEEPLY CARES ABOUT,
JUST FOR THE SAKE
OF BEING DECEITFUL.
- INDEED.
- SO IF SHE IS HIDING
SOMETHING FROM YOU,
I'M SURE THERE'S A PERFECTLY
GOOD REASON FOR IT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO TRY
A LESS "IN YOUR FACE"
APPROACH.
- HUH?
- ( dings )
- WELL...
IF YOU'RE REALLY
THAT CONCERNED,
MAYBE SOMEONE ELSE
CAN ASK HER FOR YOU.
- ( gasps )
- Wilhelmina:
I KNOW IT WAS CHIGUSA
WHO RECOMMENDED THIS,
BUT HIM?
- Tiamat:
SADLY, WE NEED HIM.
- WHY CAN'T I JUST
ASK HER OUTRIGHT
INSTEAD OF ALL THIS
CLOAK AND DAGGER NONSENSE?
OR WAS THAT PART
MY MOM'S IDEA TOO?
- I AM ATTEMPTING
A MORE HANDS-OFF APPROACH.
INDEED, DIRECT CONTACT
HAS ONLY PUT HER ON THE
DEFENSIVE.
JUST BE CAREFUL,
AND TRY TO MASK YOUR PRESENCE.
- Tiamat: FOCUS.
- RIGHT.  FOCUS.
- Wilhelmina: ANY CHANGE
IN HER BEHAVIOR AT SCHOOL?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
- IS THERE INDEED NO CHANGE?
OR ARE YOU SIMPLY
NOT NOTICING?
- NO, YOU'VE GOT IT
ALL WRONG.
NOT A DAY GOES BY
THAT I DON'T NOTICE SHANA--
( clears throat )
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW SHE WAS
HIDING ANYTHING FROM YOU,
OR THAT SHE WASN'T
GOING STRAIGHT HOME.
YOU WERE WATCHING US,
WEREN'T YOU?
WE SPLIT UP AT THE SAME PLACE
WE ALWAYS DO.
SEE YOU, SHANA.
- BYE.
- SO, YEAH.
I GUESS THAT MEANS SHE'S
HIDING SOMETHING FROM ME TOO.
- ( sighs )
- Tiamat: IT WOULD SEEM SO.
- Wilhelmina:
PERHAPS THE MADAM'S
CHOICE OF ACCOMPLICE
IS INDEED APPROPRIATE.
- MAYBE SHE TOOK
A LITTLE DETOUR?
I'M SURE YOU'RE
MISTAKEN TO WORRY ABOUT--
- ( groans )
- OR NOT.  IT'S COOL.
- THESE "LITTLE THINGS,"
IGNORING THEM INDEED
COMES BACK TO HAUNT YOU.
- Tiamat:
LITTLE THINGS MATTER.
- YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
OF COURSE.
- HER DELINQUENCY
IS TROUBLING.
IF IT COMES AS A RESULT
OF HER CURRENT LIFESTYLE,
THEN I MAY INDEED
BE FORCED TO REASSESS
THE WAY SHE'S ALLOWED
TO INTERACT IN THIS WORLD.
- "REASSESS"?
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
HANG ON,
YOU'RE NOT THINKING
ABOUT MAKING HER
QUIT SCHOOL, ARE YOU?
- YES, I AM.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT HER.
IT'S ABOUT PROTECTING
THE TREASURE TOOL INSIDE YOU.
- OH, MAN.
- END OF CONVERSATION.
INDEED, NOW IS THE TIME
FOR ACTION, NOT TALK.
- FINE.
UH...
- Wilhelmina:
WHAT IS THE MATTER NOW?
- Tiamat:
SPIT IT OUT, YOUNG MAN.
- YEAH, SORRY.
GUESS I LOST TRACK OF HER.
- Wilhelmina: SO YOU'RE SAYING
IT WASN'T THAT YOU WERE UNABLE
TO SENSE HER PRESENCE,
IT'S THAT SHE HAD INTENTIONALLY
CONCEALED IT FROM YOU?
- YEAH.
SUDDENLY, IT JUST VANISHED.
THERE'S ONLY ONE PERSON I KNOW
WHO CAN DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- A LOGICAL DEDUCTION,
INDEED.
- ( doorbell rings )
- Sato: YEAH?
- HEY, IS MARGERY HOME?
WE NEED TO ASK HER SOMETHING.
- YEAH.  THE THING IS,
SHE'S BEEN HITTING
THE BOTTLE SINCE NOON.
THREATENED DEATH IF I WOKE HER
FOR ANYTHING BUT A DENIZEN.
SO, UNLESS IT'S SOME KIND OF
EMERGENCY OR SOMETHING...
- IT IS, INDEED.
- Tiamat: HIGH PRIORITY.
- WHAT?  WILHELMINA.
- WHAT'S THE ISSUE?
- Tiamat: CARE TO JOIN US?
- ( sighs )
- WAS IT NOT INDEED
YOUR IDEA TO COME HERE?
- LISTEN, I CAN TELL
FROM HOW SATO'S ACTING,
WHATEVER'S GOING ON,
MARGERY'S TOTALLY IN ON IT.
THOSE TWO ARE USUALLY
AT EACH OTHER'S THROATS
LIKE CATS AND DOGS,
WHICH MEANS THEY'RE DOING
SOMEONE ELSE A FAVOR.
AND THAT SOMEONE
WANTED US TO COME HERE.
IT WAS ALL
PART OF THE PLAN.
IF WE DID TALK TO MARGERY,
SHE'D PROBABLY JUST LIE TO US
OR LEAD US IN CIRCLES.
AND SINCE THE DIRECT APPROACH
HASN'T BEEN WORKING,
LET'S TRY IT
THE SNEAKY WAY.
NOTHING.
NOT A TRACE OF HER.
- Wilhelmina:
I'D SAY THAT'S NOT SURPRISING
SINCE SHE'S CONCEALING
HER PRESENCE FROM US.
- Tiamat: OBVIOUSLY.
- THANK GOODNESS.
- HMM?
- UH, NO...
NOT THANK GOODNESS
ABOUT HER HIDING.
I MEAN, SINCE THE TUNING,
NO OTHER TORCHES HAVE
SHOWN UP BESIDES ME.
- Wilhelmina:
THOSE WERE TRUE WORDS OF RELIEF.
I DETECTED NO TRACE
OF SELFISHNESS
OR SELF PITY.
NO ENVY OR SCORN
TOWARDS OTHERS.
HOW CAN HE PERCEIVE
THE WORLD THE WAY HE DOES?
IS IT POSSIBLE HE IS
THAT RARE TYPE OF PERSON
FOR WHOM MOTIVATION
IS NOT DRIVEN BY EMOTION,
NO MATTER WHAT PERIL
HE MAY BE FACING?
IF SO, IT EXPLAINS
WHY HE IS SLOW TO REACT
IN TYPICALLY EMOTIONALLY
CHARGED SITUATIONS.
- Tiamat:
IS THAT TOO EASY?
- ( gasps )
INDEED.
I HAVE PLENTY OF TIME
TO SOLVE THAT MYSTERY.
- WILHELMINA, WHAT ABOUT HER
UNRESTRICTED SPELL?
SHE CAN'T HIDE ITS ENERGY,
SO IF SHE'S USING IT,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO FIND HER.
- LET'S SEE WHAT
I CAN REVEAL.
- ( both gasp )
- WHO CAST ALL THESE?
MARGERY, I'M GUESSING?
- IT WOULD INDEED SEEM SO.
- Yuji: SEE YOU, WILHELMINA.
I'LL BE SURE TO ASK HER
AT SCHOOL TOMORROW.
DON'T WORRY,
I'M SURE SHE'S NOT
DOING ANYTHING BAD.
IF IT'S SOME KIND OF SECRET,
I MIGHT BE ABLE TO
GET HER TO LET ME IN ON IT.
- Ogata: SORRY, SAKAI.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN TODAY.
- HUH?
- WE'RE STEALING SHANA
AWAY FROM YOU
SO THE THREE OF US CAN
GO SHOPPING TOGETHER.
- YEP. NO BOYS ALLOWED.
SORRY.
- UH...
- ( sighs )
FIRST SATO,
AND NOW YOSHIDA AND OGATA
ARE IN ON...
SHANA'S BIG SECRET.
MAYBE THEY'RE PLANNING
LIKE A SURPRISE PARTY
FOR WILHELMINA OR SOMETHING.
BUT WHY WOULDN'T THEY
TELL ME?
I GUESS THEY THOUGHT THAT
IF WILHELMINA THREATENED ME,
I'D CAVE AND SPILL THE BEANS.
NAH.  MIGHT BE GETTING
AHEAD OF MYSELF
ON THE WHOLE "PARTY" THEORY.
- Ike: MAN, YOU'RE EVEN
WALKING HOME ALONE?
LOOKED LIKE SHANA SPENT
THE WHOLE DAY TRYING TO
AVOID YOU.
- UM, YEAH.
IT'S LIKE THERE'S
SOME KIND OF BIG SECRET.
EVERYONE I TRY
AND ASK ABOUT IT
JUST DODGES THE QUESTION.
I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU MIGHT HAVE HEARD ANYTHING?
I DON'T KNOW,
LIKE A SURPRISE PARTY
THEY'RE THROWING FOR
WILHELMINA OR SOMETHING?
- UH...
NO, UH-UH.
BUT YOU DO HAVE TO WONDER,
IF I'M IN ON IT TOO,
WOULD I REALLY GIVE YOU
A TRUTHFUL ANSWER?
OR WOULD I TRY AND
THROW YOU OFF,
AND THEN JUST REPORT
EVERYTHING BACK TO SHANA?
QUITE A CONUNDRUM.
- UH...
- Wilhelmina:
I WOULD LIKE AN EXPLANATION.
WHAT REASON WOULD THEY HAVE
TO BE IN SUCH AN ESTABLISHMENT?
- Yuji: WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"REASON"?
THEY'RE JUST HERE TO SHOP.
- THE PURCHASE OF FOOD STUFFS
AND ALL OTHER REQUIRED
HOUSEHOLD ITEMS
IS MY RESPONSIBILITY.
- Tiamat:
SHE RUNS A TIGHT SHIP.
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT IS FUNNY?
- OH, NOTHING.
I WAS JUST THINKING
THAT THIS KIND OF REMINDS ME
OF BACK WHEN
SHE AND I FIRST MET.
HEY, WILHELMINA,
YOU'D PREFER IF SHE WENT BACK
TO THE WAY SHE WAS, HUH?
THE DEAD SERIOUS FLAME HAZE
I MET THAT DAY.
WAS SHE ALWAYS LIKE THAT,
EVEN WHEN SHE WAS
A LITTLE GIRL?
- OH, YES, INDEED.
SERIOUS DEMEANOR ON MISSIONS,
TRAINING EVERY DAY,
SELF-DISCIPLINE--
THAT HAS NO BEARING
ON ANY OF THIS.
- Tiamat: INCONSEQUENTIAL.
- HUH?
- WILHELMINA, HOLD ON.
DON'T YOU STAND OUT A BIT?
- ( sighs )
- UM, NOT THAT YOU LOOK BAD.
BUT DON'T YOU EVER
WEAR ANYTHING ELSE?
- I REQUESTED A GARMENT
WORN BY THOSE WHO WORK
IN THE SERVICE OF NOBLES.
THIS IS INDEED THE STYLE
I WAS TOLD I SHOULD WEAR.
I FIND IT BOTH
FUNCTIONAL AND COMFORTABLE.
THEREFORE,
I HAVE CHOSEN TO WEAR IT
EVER SINCE LEAVING
TENDOU-KYU.
- SO WHEN--
WHEN IT WAS JUST
THE TWO OF YOU,
OR FOUR, I GUESS,
DID YOU GUYS EVER
GET BORED OR LONELY?
LIKE AROUND THE HOLIDAYS
AND STUFF?
- THERE WERE FIVE OF US.
- UH-- REALLY?
- ( clears throat )
NOW BE SILENT, BOY.
- Tiamat: MANNERS.
- SORRY.
- DID WE GET EVERYTHING?
- UM, YEAH.
I THINK WE DID.
- Ogata:
WELL SHANA, GOOD LUCK.
- Shana:
THANKS AGAIN, BOTH OF YOU.
- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE SHE WAS JUST
TAGGING ALONG WITH
THE OTHER TWO.
- 'KAY, BETTER RUN.
SEE YOU.
- UH, WILHELMINA?
AAH!
( grunts )
( coughs )
- I SAID BE SILENT.
- Tiamat:
SHE SAID IT TWICE NOW.
- WE SHOULD INDEED
FOLLOW HER FROM ABOVE
SO WE DON'T LOSE
VISUAL CONTACT.
- ( grunts )
- Wilhelmina:
WHY IS SHE GOING THIS FAR?
- Yuji:
WHY ARE YOU GOING THIS FAR?
I DON'T GET IT.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU DON'T TRUST HER.
AND YOU ALSO KNOW
SHE DOESN'T TAKE
THE DUTIES OF
A FLAME HAZE LIGHTLY.
SO I DON'T GET IT.
THIS ONE TIME,
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST LET IT GO?
- REGRET.
- WHAT?
- I DON'T WANT HER
TO GET HURT.
BECAUSE KEEPING FOOLISH SECRETS
ONLY CAUSES REGRET.
I KNOW THAT PAIN
FROM ALL THE SECRETS
I KEPT FROM THE ENGAGED LINK.
SO I WORRY.
HOW WILL THIS AFFECT HER?
HAS SHE NOT BEGUN
TO FEEL REGRET
OVER KEEPING SECRETS,
EVEN SMALL ONES?
- WILHELMINA...
Yuji: HONESTLY,
I THINK SHE HAS CHANGED
SINCE I FIRST MET HER.
HAVING LIVED HERE
FOR A WHILE,
IT'S LIKE SHE'S...
SHE'S...
MATURED.
I THINK IT'S BECAUSE
SHE'S FACED THE SAME
FEARS AS YOU,
AND SOME YOU HAVEN'T.
BUT SOMEWHERE IN
ALL THAT CHAOS,
SHE FOUND SOMETHING
SHE CARES ABOUT
TO HOLD ONTO.
EVEN RIGHT NOW TOO,
I'LL BET.
- ( sighs )
- HIDEY-HO!
SO, I HEARD YOU TWO
DROPPED BY EARLIER
WHILE I WAS ASLEEP.
- Marcosias:
( laughing )
I THINK "BLACKED OUT"
IS WHAT YOU MEAN.
- SHUT UP, STUPID MARCO.
( groans )
- WHAT IS THIS INDEED
ALL ABOUT?
- WHAT IS WHAT ALL ABOUT?
- WELL, TO BEGIN WITH,
DID YOU GIVE HER A BOOKMARK
THAT CAN CONCEAL HER
PRESENCE FROM US?
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
I KNOW WHO CAN DO THAT.
- HUH?  WHO IS "HER"?
- Marcosias:  SHEESH.
YEAH, WE GAVE HER ONE.
SHE ASKED FOR IT.
GUESS IT'S ALL THE RAGE
THESE DAYS
FOR YOUNGSTERS TO
SNEAK AROUND
BEHIND THEIR PARENTAL-TYPES'
BACKS AFTER SCHOOL.
( chuckles )
- Tiamat: YOU'RE NOT HELPFUL.
- WHICH INDEED
BEGS THE QUESTION,
WHY IS SOMEONE LIKE YOU
HELPING IN A MATTER LIKE THIS?
- BECAUSE SOMEONE LIKE ME
WAS IN THE MOOD
TO DO SOMETHING NICE.
- Marcosias: I DON'T SEE
WHY WE'RE IN TROUBLE
FOR GIVING HER A MEASLY
LITTLE BOOKMARK.
OH RIGHT, THE SUPER POWERFUL
UNRESTRICTED SPELL ON IT.
( laughing )
- SORRY.  RUNNING BEHIND.
- IT'S OKAY.
- BUT DON'T STOP NOW.
IT'S ALMOST TIME.
- I KNOW.
- YOU PRACTICED
FOR A WHOLE WEEK
TO GET ALL OF THIS
DOWN PAT.
WE HAVE TO FINISH EVERYTHING
BEFORE WILHELMINA GETS HOME.
- OTHERWISE, IT WON'T BE
MUCH OF A SURPRISE.
- RIGHT.
- HEY, BY THE WAY,
WHAT IS TODAY?
I MEAN, WHAT MAKES IT
SO SIGNIFICANT FOR WILHELMINA?
- I'M NOT SURE.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
I HEARD WILHELMINA MENTION
IT WAS A SPECIAL DAY.
- IS IT HER BIRTHDAY?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- WELL, WHATEVER.
IT'S SPECIAL IS
ALL THAT MATTERS.
- ( gasps )
- KAZUMI, WHAT IS IT?
- THE FLOUR.
THE KIND YOU GOT IS WRONG.
- ( both gasp )
- SEE?  WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
I KNEW SHE'D
PLAY DUMB WITH US.
WE NEED PROOF.
THAT WAY SHE CAN'T WEASEL
OUT OF TELLING US
WHAT WE WANT TO KNOW.
- I WILL INDEED GET
A STRAIGHT ANSWER
OUT OF YOU AT SOME POINT.
- Tiamat: LIKE IT OR NOT.
- ( chuckles )
- ( yelps )
( screams )
- ( chuckles )
YES?  SOMETHING UP?
- Kazumi: I'M SO SORRY,
MARGERY,
BUT WE'VE HAD A MIX-UP
WITH THE GROCERY SHOPPING.
CAN YOU PLEASE BUY US
A LITTLE MORE TIME?
15 MINUTES SHOULD BE
ABOUT RIGHT.
- Tanaka:
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I CAN'T HOLD OFF WILHELMINA
ALL BY MYSELF.
- Margery:
NO CHOICE, KIDDO.
WE'RE NOT GOING DOWN
THIS LATE IN THE GAME.
- YEAH, BUT--
- ( crashing )
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
I KNEW IT.
YOU'VE HAD ME FOLLOWING
WILHELMINA AROUND
SO YOU COULD TRACK
WHERE SHE IS.
- ( murmurs )
- Yuji:
SO TANAKA WAS IN CHARGE OF
REPORTING OUR MOVEMENTS
BACK TO SHANA.
THAT MEANS THE PERSON
WHO SET US UP TOGETHER
IS IN ON IT TOO.
MY MOM.
- SO SORRY, YUJI.
- ( sighs )
THIS IS JUST CRUEL.
WHAT THE HECK ARE
YOU GUYS PLANNING ALREADY?
- OKAY, FINE.
I'LL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
IT ALL BEGAN
ON A COLD WINTER'S MORN.
ICY WIND UPON MY CHEEK.
THE WIND WAS SO STRONG,
EVERY TREE IN TOWN
HAD ALL THEIR LEAVES
BLOWN OFF.
EVERY ONE,
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
IT WAS LIKE...
REALLY REALLY COLD.
OR, UM...
WAS IT A SUMMER AFTERNOON.
YES, WITH THE HOT SUN
BEATING DOWN.
I REMEMBER THE WATERMELON
WAS PARTICULARLY GOOD THAT DAY.
OH, SILLY ME,
IT WAS SPRING.
I'M SORRY, NO, AUTUMN,
MIDNIGHT IN MONSOON SEASON,
WHEN SATO SAID TO ME
"HEY, HUNGRY, BRO?"
TO WHICH I REPLIED
"YEAH, DUDE."
I HAD CROQUETTE SOBA.
SATO HAD SALMON RICE,
AND OGATA...
SHE WENT WITH THE OMELET.
AND AFTER THAT--!
- IS THERE INDEED
A POINT HERE?
- Tiamat: SPIT IT OUT.
- WELL, YOU SEE...
I, UM...
- ( gasps )
WE'RE BACK.
- ( murmurs )
- ( phone rings )
- ( chuckles nervously )
- ( phone beeps )
OH, THANK GOD.
SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS.
ALASTOR AND MARGERY
CAN EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
FOR REAL THIS TIME.
PLEASE, IF YOU WOULD
MAKE YOUR WAY BACK TO
THE HIRAI RESIDENCE.
- ALASTOR?
- HIRAI RESIDENCE?
- Tiamat: SOUNDS SUSPICIOUS.
- TELL HER I EXPECT TO BE
WELL PAID FOR ALL THIS.
- Wilhelmina: WE INDEED TOOK
THE SCENIC ROUTE TO
GET TO THE ANSWER.
- ( Yuji sighs )
- Kazumi and Ogata:
WELCOME HOME, WILHELMINA.
- Yuji: YOSHIDA, OGATA?
- ALL RIGHT,
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
- COME IN AND HAVE A SEAT.
WE'LL TELL YOU MORE THERE.
- OH, YOU CAN COME TOO,
SAKAI.
- OHH...
- WELCOME HOME.
- JEEZ. TRYING TO HIDE
SOMETHING FROM YOU IS TOUGH.
I GUESS WE'RE JUST LUCKY
NOBODY GOT HURT.
WE STUCK YUJI ON YOU
AS SOON AS WE KNEW
YOU WERE SUSPICIOUS.
ALL OF US KNEW WHERE
YOU WERE AT ALL TIMES.
- ( Marcosias chuckles )
- LETTING US TELL YOU
WHAT WE WANTED,
WHEN WE WANTED.
- ( chuckles )
OW!
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE
MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
I'LL BRING KEISAKU
HIS PAYOFF
FOR HIS LITTLE PART
IN ALL THIS.
- ( door opens, closes )
- WILHELMINA,
SHANA WORKED REALLY
HARD ON THIS MEAL.
SHE EVEN GOT KAZUMI
TO TRAIN HER AND EVERYTHING.
- YEP.  ALL I DID
WAS PICK THE INGREDIENTS.
OH, AND STOOD BY TO MAKE SURE
NOTHING CAUGHT ON FIRE.
RIGHT, SHANA?
- UH-HUH.
( giggles )
- COOL.  I'LL BE IN CHARGE
OF TAKING TANAKA HIS SHARE
OF THE FOOD.
- AND I'LL BRING IKE HIS.
- OF COURSE.
I KNEW THOSE GUYS
WERE IN ON IT.
- SORRY, SAKAI.
TIME FOR YOU TO GO TOO.
- WAIT, WHAT?
- HERE, SAKAI.
THANK YOUR MOM AGAIN
FOR ALL HER HELP.
- OH.
- ( chuckles )
- SO, WILHELMINA,
WHAT YOU TOLD ME EARLIER
ABOUT SCHOOL?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- ( chuckles )
THANKS, WILHELMINA.
- ( door opens, closes )
- Wilhelmina:
IS THIS INDEED PANNENKOEKEN?
- Shana: YEP.
- Tiamat: ASK HER THE REASON.
- I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
WHY YOU FELT I NEEDED
THE MYSTES LIKE AN ALBATROSS
AROUND MY NECK
THROUGH ALL THIS.
YET YOU FIND IT
PERFECTLY FINE
TO SIMPLY
SEND HIM ON HIS WAY?
- Alastor: IT IS FINE.
IN FACT, IT BEHOOVES HIM
TO KEEP HIM IN THE DARK.
- HMM?
- ALASTOR AND I THOUGHT
IT WAS PRETTY LOUSY
THAT YOU AND YUJI
WEREN'T GETTING ALONG,
SINCE WE'RE
STUCK WITH HIM.
- Alastor:
WE CAME TO AN AGREEMENT.
IN ORDER TO REMAIN VIGILANT
AGAINST FUTURE CRISES,
WE NEED TO WORK TO ESTABLISH
A MODICUM OF TRUST
AMONGST THE CORE GROUP.
AFTER SPENDING
TIME WITH HIM,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF YUJI SAKAI?
- HE IS A UNIQUE BOY,
INDEED.
- ( chuckles )
OKAY, OKAY.
ENOUGH TALK.
GO ON, WILHELMINA,
DIG IN.
( gasps )
WELL?
- IT'S DELICIOUS.
- ( chuckles )
- Tiamat:
I'VE GOT FOOD ENVY.
- ( chuckles )
HEY, WILHELMINA,
THE GIRLS ASKED EARLIER
AND I WASN'T SURE.
WHAT DAY IS TODAY?
YOU SAID IT WAS SPECIAL,
DIDN'T YOU?
- HAS IT BEEN SO LONG
THAT YOU'VE FORGOTTEN?
- ( murmurs )
I GUESS?
( giggles )
HEY, WILHELMINA!
ARE THERE ANY OTHER DAYS
YOU WANT TO REMEMBER?
( giggles )
'KAY.
- TODAY MARKS...
THE DAY YOU ENTERED MY LIFE.
SPECIAL INDEED.
- ( chuckles )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )