- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- JUNKO, WOULD YOU...
- HUH?
- GO OUT... WITH ME?
- SURE.
- ( chuckles )
- ( giggles )
- ( sighs )
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT
THAT JUNKO
WOULD END UP WITH
SUCH A HOTTIE?
- RIGHT?  GUESS HAMAGUCHI
LIKES THE QUIET TYPE.
THEY REALLY DO MAKE
A CUTE COUPLE THOUGH.
- THEY DO!
I'VE NEVER SEEN
JUNKO SO HAPPY.
- WELL, HE'S LUCKY,
'CAUSE SHE WAS ABOUT
TO GIVE UP ON HIM.
- ( beeping )
- WHERE TO?
WANT TO GO TO JOUSHI PARK?
YOU SAID THE ICE CREAM
THERE IS AWESOME.
I'D LIKE TO
GIVE IT A TRY.
- HMM.  SOUNDS GOOD.
- UH-- HEY,
YOU'RE WEARING IT.
- YEAH, I PROBABLY
SHOULD HAVE WAITED
TO WEAR IT WITH
A NICER OUTFIT,
BUT I COULDN'T
HELP MYSELF.
- I'M STILL NOT SURE
WHAT KIND OF STUFF YOU LIKE.
I DID OKAY ON
THAT ONE THEN?
- MM-HMM.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
IT MUST HAVE
BEEN EXPENSIVE.
- WELL, YEAH.
I HAD NO IDEA
JEWELRY WAS SO PRICEY.
BUT AS LONG AS YOU LIKE IT.
- YEAH, I LOVE IT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- UH?  THE LIGHT.
- LET'S GO.
- ( pop music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- AWESOME, THANKS.
TODAY WAS A BLAST.
- WHO KNEW THERE WERE
SO MANY THINGS TO DO HERE?
- WE SHOULD COME BACK.
- NEXT TIME, WE'LL HAVE TO
MAKE A DAY OF IT
INSTEAD OF JUST
DROPPING BY AFTER SCHOOL.
- HMM!
- YOU FREE SATURDAY?
- YOU BET.
- HOW ABOUT SUNDAY?
- YEAH, I'M FREE.
- OKAY.
WHAT ABOUT THE FOLLOWING
WEEKEND?
- ALL YOURS.
- WHAT ARE YOUR SUMMER
AND WINTER BREAKS LOOKING LIKE?
DO YOU HAVE ANY PLANS
FOR CHRISTMAS YET?
- THAT'S MONTHS FROM NOW.
- JUST CHECKING.
- Junko: I HOPE WE STAY
TOGETHER FOREVER, HAMAGUCHI.
- Hamaguchi: FOREVER, HUH?
THAT'S A LONG TIME.
- ( gasps )
- JUNKO?
- KISSING A BOY IN PUBLIC?
HOW COULD YOU
BE SO SHAMELESS?
- I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
- YOU'RE STILL A CHILD.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
MAKING OUT WITH A BOY.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
THEY'RE ONLY AFTER
ONE THING.
- HAMAGUCHI ISN'T LIKE
THE OTHER BOYS!
- IF THAT WERE TRUE,
HE'D KNOW BETTER THAN
TO EVEN TRY.
- IT IS TRUE! YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT HIM!
- NO, WAIT.
- LET GO!
( gasps, groans )
- ( gasps )
JUNKO?
- THIS BRACELET HOLDS
NO INFORMATION ABOUT
THE DENIZEN.
- Alastor: EVIDENTLY,
THE GIRL'S SOUL WAS CONSUMED
WITHOUT HER EVEN
REALIZING IT.
- THE ONLY TIME SHE
COULD HAVE BEEN ATTACKED
WAS WHEN SHE WAS
WITH HAMAGUCHI.
- CAN YOU EXCUSE ME?
- MM-HMM.
- BE RIGHT BACK.
WAIT HERE.
- OKAY.
- EXCUSE ME, MAY I HAVE
A MOMENT OF YOUR TIME?
- HUH?
- I'M A PROFESSIONAL
PHOTOGRAPHER IN TOWN,
AND I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR MALE MODELS.
I'D LIKE TO TAKE
SOME SHOTS OF YOU.
- UH...
- YOU'VE GOT A GREAT LOOK,
AND I'D LOVE TO
CAPTURE IT ON FILM.
IT WON'T TAKE LONG.
HOW ABOUT IT?
- I'M WITH MY GIRLFRIEND.
- WE CAN WRAP IT UP
WHENEVER SHE RETURNS.
- WELL...
Hamaguchi:
HE'S CREEPY LOOKING,
BUT HE SEEMS LEGIT.
I GUESS IT'LL BE COOL
TILL JUNKO GETS BACK.
OKAY, I'LL DO IT.
- MUCH OBLIGED.
- ( camera shutter clicks )
- THE CAMERA LOVES YOU,
YOUNG MAN.
THANKS AGAIN.
I GOT SOME FANTASTIC STUFF.
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO WITH THE PICTURES?
ARE THEY FOR A MAGAZINE?
- WELL, UH...
- IF THEY'RE PRINTED,
I'D LIKE TO PICK ONE UP.
- COULD YOU COME BACK TOMORROW
AND POSE SOME MORE FOR ME?
SCHOOL UNIFORM'S NOT BAD,
BUT I'D LIKE TO SHOOT YOU
IN SOMETHING TRENDY.
SAY YES, AND I'LL NOT ONLY
GIVE YOU THE PICTURES
WE'VE TAKEN TODAY,
BUT I'LL PAY YOU A SMALL
STIPEND FOR YOUR TIME.
- SERIOUSLY?
OHH, I HAVE TO GO
TO SCHOOL TOMORROW.
BUT I COULD DO SATURDAY?
- THAT WORKS FOR ME.
SEE YOU THEN.
YOU WON'T REGRET IT.
- Shana: BY THE TIME
YUKIO HAMAGUCHI
FINALLY FOUND JUNKO OGAMI...
- Alastor: SHE HAD ALREADY
BECOME A TORCH.
- HER SOUL MUST
HAVE BEEN CONSUMED
WHILE HE WAS BEING
DISTRACTED.
I SUSPECT THE PHOTOGRAPHER
IS OUR DENIZEN.
SEEMS AN ODD CHOICE
OF HOBBY THOUGH.
- Alastor:
THERE ARE DENIZEN
WHO HAVE USED THEIR
LOVE OF ART
TO LURE IN PREY.
IT APPEARS THAT IS EXACTLY
WHAT THIS PHOTOGRAPHER IS
ATTEMPTING TO DO.
- HMM.
HOWEVER,
IT DOES NOT EXPLAIN WHY
JUNKO OGAMI'S SOUL
WAS CONSUMED,
AND YUKIO HAMAGUCHI'S WAS NOT.
- Alastor:
OR THE MYSTERY OF
THE AMERICAN TORCH.
PERHAPS WHEN WE MEET
WITH YUKIO HAMAGUCHI
AND THE PHOTOGRAPHER
TOMORROW,
OUR QUESTIONS
WILL BE ANSWERED.
- ( sighs )
THAT BRACELET IS
OF NO USE TO ME.
- JUNKO?
FORGET SOMETHING?
IF YOU'RE MEETING HAMAGUCHI,
YOU SHOULD WEAR THIS.
- ( chuckles )
- OH.
YOU READY TO GO?
- YEAH.
- Hamaguchi: MAN, I'M GLAD
SHE DECIDED TO COME ALONG.
I KNOW, I'LL ASK TO TAKE
A PHOTO OF US TOGETHER.
- Shana: I CAN DEFINITELY
SENSE A DENIZEN IN THIS CITY.
BUT IT SEEMS TO BE
RATHER WEAK.
IT MUST BE AWARE OF
MY PRESENCE AS WELL.
WHY HASN'T IT SHOWN ITSELF?
IT DOES NOT APPEAR TO HAVE
ATTACKED ANY MORE HUMANS.
I WONDER WHAT IT'S AFTER.
WHAT?
- NOTHING.
YOU JUST HAD A WEIRD
LOOK ON YOUR FACE.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE HAVING FUN.
- Shana: HAVING FUN?
- YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO COME ALONG
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
I CAN GO ALONE.
IT'S COOL EITHER WAY.
- NO, I WANT TO.
- OKAY.
- Shana: I JUST CAN'T
LET HIM SUSPECT ME.
I HAVE TO MIMIC
JUNKO OGAMI TO
SET HIM AT EASE.
WHAT CAN I DO
TO MAKE HIM HAPPY?
- UH--
( chuckles )
HUH?
YOUR BRACELET?
- MY MOTHER WAS
ABLE TO FIX IT.
- OH, GOOD.
SO YOU MADE UP WITH HER.
I'M REALLY GLAD.
- Shana:
I WILL FIND THIS DENIZEN.
- HUH.  I GUESS
HE HASN'T MADE IT YET.
- THIS IS WHERE
YOU ARE TO MEET HIM?
- YOU'RE SO FORMAL.
YEAH.
HE'S PROBABLY JUST
RUNNING A LITTLE LATE.
WANT TO HAVE A SEAT
WHILE WE WAIT?
HERE YOU ARE, MILADY.
- THANKS.
CAN YOU SHOW ME WHERE
YOU FOUND ME SPACING OUT?
- OH, IT WAS OVER THERE
IN FRONT OF THAT LAKE.
- Shana: SO CLOSE.
NO MORE THAN 15
OR 16 METERS.
- I'LL GET US SOME DRINKS.
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE?
- A NON-CARBONATED
BEVERAGE, PLEASE.
NOTHING TOO SOUR,
AND I PREFER
NATURAL FRUIT FLAVORS.
- UH, WHAT?
- JUST GET ME SOME FRUIT JUICE.
- AS YOU WISH.
SIT TIGHT.
- WELL, ALASTOR,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- Alastor: THEY WERE IN
SUCH CLOSE PROXIMITY.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
THE PHOTOGRAPHER.
I SUSPECT THE DENIZEN
CAST A SEAL
ENTRAPPING BOTH
YUKIO HAMAGUCHI,
AND JUNKO OGAMI.
BUT WHY WAS ONLY
ONE OF THEIR SOULS CONSUMED?
- SERIOUSLY.
IT JUST DOES NOT MAKE ANY SENSE.
- Alastor:
THERE MUST BE A REASON.
BUT WE HAVE NO WAY
OF KNOWING,
SHORT OF ASKING
THE DENIZEN ITSELF.
HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE
TO SENSE ITS PRESENCE?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
AND I FIND THAT
DISTURBING.
( gasps )
NO WAY.
HAMAGUCHI'S VANISHED.
- Alastor: WHAT?
- HE'S GONE.
I TOOK MY EYES OFF HIM
FOR A SPLIT SECOND.
- Alastor: A HUMAN CANNOT
MOVE THAT FAST.
IT'S HERE!
- YOU SEE THAT?
IT LEFT US A TRAIL.
( grunts )
- Alastor:
EVEN THE MOST POWERFUL DENIZEN
WOULD NEVER BE BRAZEN ENOUGH
TO LEAVE BEHIND
SUCH AN OBVIOUS TRAIL.
- HE WAS ABDUCTED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME,
AND I DID NOT
SENSE ANYTHING.
WHICH CONFIRMS HOW WEAK
IT MUST BE.
- Alastor:
IT MUST HAVE A DEATH WISH
IF IT HAS THE AUDACITY
TO ABDUCT SOMEONE
IN FRONT OF A FLAME HAZE.
- DAMMIT.
I SHOULD HAVE WATCHED HIM.
THAT'S THEM.
- Alastor: RIDICULOUS.
IT'S TRYING TO
ESCAPE IN A TRUCK?
- WISHFUL THINKING.
( grunts )
( gasps )
A SEAL?
ARE THOSE PHOTOGRAPHS?
- IF IT ISN'T
THE FLAMAING-HAIRED,
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER...
- Alastor:
IDENTIFY YOURSELF.
WHAT IS THE MEANING
OF THIS?
- ( chuckles )
AND OF COURSE,
SHE'S JOINED BY
THE GREAT FLAME OF HEAVEN.
( laughs )
THESE PHOTOGRAPHS
BELONG TO ME...
THE RELISHING EMBRACE,
UKOBACH.
- UKOBACH?
- Alastor: I HAVE NEVER
HEARD THAT NAME.
- WELL, NOW YOU HAVE.
ONE DAY IT WILL BE SYNONYMOUS
WITH UNLIMITED POWER AND BEAUTY.
- Alastor:
YOUR FORM IS SO PRIMITIVE
IT'S NO WONDER WE
COULD NOT SENSE YOUR PRESENCE.
- I AM IN THE MIDST OF
SEARCHING FOR A NEW ONE.
I'VE BEEN COLLECTING
THESE ATTRACTIVE YOUNG MEN
SO I COULD COMBINE
THEIR BEST FEATURES
TO CREATE THE PERFECT FORM.
- THAT IS WHY YOU'VE
COME TO THIS WORLD?
I FIND YOUR REASONING
ABSOLUTELY DESPICABLE.
- Alastor: A DENIZEN'S FORM
MUST MATCH ITS TRUE NATURE.
- YES.
SOME DAY I'LL TAKE ON
A FORM I FIND FITTING.
- IT WON'T WORK.
YOU'RE TOO WEAK.
- EXCUSE ME?
- NORMALLY I'M ABLE
TO SENSE THE PRESENCE
OF EVEN THE WEAKEST
OF DENIZEN.
HOWEVER, YOUR PRESENCE
WAS NO STRONGER THAN
THE HUMANS'.
- ( gasps )
- YOU ARE SO WEAK,
EVEN IF YOU WERE CAPABLE
OF CREATING THE PERFECT FORM,
YOU WOULD NEVER HAVE
THE STRENGTH TO SUSTAIN IT.
FROM WHAT I CAN TELL,
YOUR CURRENT FORM
IS ALREADY A PERFECT FIT
FOR YOUR TRUE NATURE,
A HIDEOUS BLOB.
- ( growls )
- GIVE UP.
YOUR ATTACKS ARE NO MATCH
FOR THE NIETONO NO SHANA.
- ( sighs )
- GO BACK TO THE CRIMSON WORLD.
YOUR SEARCH FOR
A NEW FORM IS FUTILE.
YOU'VE DONE NOTHING
BUT CAUSE HUMANS
PAIN AND SUFFERING.
- ( chuckles )
YOU KNOW THIS BOY?
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
HE'S STILL ALIVE?
I USED MY TREASURE TOOL,
ATLANT,
TO CAPTURE HIM
PHOTOGRAPHICALLY
WITHOUT CAUSING HIM HARM.
- AND THE OTHERS?
- THEY'RE ALL ALIVE.
THEY'VE SIMPLY BEEN FROZEN
IN THESE PHOTOGRAPHS.
- ( gasps )
- Alastor:
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE AMERICAN MAN
WHO WAS FOUND RECENTLY?
- HE HAD BECOME WEATHERED,
SO I CONSUMED HIS SOUL.
HONESTLY, I THOUGHT HIS
POWER OF EXISTENCE
WOULD RUN OUT
BEFORE HE WAS FOUND.
IS THAT WHY YOU'VE
COME AFTER ME?
OR IS IT BECAUSE I ALSO
CONSUMED THE SOUL
OF THIS YOUNG MAN'S
LITTLE GIRLFRIEND?
- ( grunts )
- STAY BACK,
OR I'LL KILL HIM.
- YOU SHOULD KNOW BETTER
THAN TO THREATEN A FLAME HAZE.
- IMAGINE HOW
THE WORLD'S BALANCE
WOULD BE AFFECTED
IF I CONSUMED ALL THESE
HUMAN SOULS AT ONCE.
I HAVE THE UPPER HAND,
FLAME HAZE.
ONE FALSE MOVE
AND THEY'RE DEAD,
LIKE YOU!
THEY'RE GONE.
- AAH!
- ( shouts )
- ( Ukobach groans )
- Alastor: NICE WORK.
THE HUMANS REMAIN UNHARMED,
AND THE DENIZEN'S
TREASURE TOOL IS
NOW IN OUR HANDS.
- ( sighs )
- ( car horn honks )
- Alastor: I ALMOST FORGOT
WE'RE ON A TRUCK. STOP IT!
- DAMN. AND I THOUGHT
IT WAS OVER.
- ( sighs )
I MUST HAVE DOZED OFF.
I HOPE JUNKO'S BEHAVING.
( sighs )
SHE'S NOT MY LITTLE BABY
ANYMORE.
MAYBE...
I SHOULD INVITE HIM
OVER FOR TEA ONE DAY.
CERTAINLY WOULDN'T HURT
FOR ME TO GET TO KNOW THE BOY.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
( chuckles )
LET'S NOT RUSH THINGS.
- ( siren wailing )
- ( moans )
- SPAIN-- NO, HE'S BRAZILIAN.
ANYONE HERE SPEAK
PORTUGUESE?
- I THINK THIS GUY'S
ITALIAN.
- WATER.
KEEP HIM HYDRATED.
- Hamaguchi:
WHAT HAPPENED?
HOW DID I END UP HERE?
JUNKO...
I WAS WITH JUNKO.
WHERE IS SHE?
( gasps )
( chuckles )
THANK GOODNESS.
SHE'S OKAY.
- ( chuckles )
- JUNKO.
JUNKO?
- THIS IS GOOD-BYE.
- DON'T LEAVE.
( gasps )
- ( EMTs chattering )
- Junko: I HOPE WE STAY
TOGETHER FOREVER, HAMAGUCHI.
- WHAT'S THIS?
WHERE DID IT COME FROM?
WHOA.
WHY AM I...?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, SON?
ARE YOU IN PAIN?
- UH-UH.
( crying )
- Alastor:
THIS MISSION WAS EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
- FOR YOU.
I FIND IT DIFFICULT
TO ASSIMILATE WITH
THE HUMAN BEINGS.
- Alastor:
I HAVE NO DOUBT
THAT ONE DAY
YOU WILL COME UPON A HUMAN
WHO IS ABLE TO
RELATE TO YOU.
- MAYBE SO.
BUT THAT MAY ONLY
CAUSE MORE TROUBLE.
I HOPE ON OUR NEXT MISSION,
I'LL GET THE CHANCE
TO FIGHT A CRIMSON LORD.
- ( Alastor chuckles )
- Shana: OTO.
AND AFTER THAT,
WE'LL REACH MISAKI.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Shana: THIS IS THE PLACE THAT
FIRST BROUGHT US TOGETHER.
MISAKI CITY.
SINCE THE DAY WE MET,
WE'VE FOUGHT COUNTLESS
BATTLES TOGETHER.
BUT IT HASN'T ALWAYS
BEEN ABOUT THE FIGHT.
THEN ONE DAY,
EVERYTHING CHANGED.
SO WE MEET AGAIN.
YUJI.