- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Junko: I KNOW, NEXT TIME
I'LL ASK HAMAGUCHI TO COME
WITH ME.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- I AM A FLAME HAZE.
- A WHAT?
- I AM THE FLAM HAZE
OF THE NIETONO NO SHANA.
- ( gasps )
- Junko:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
WHY AM I SO SCARED
OF A LITTLE GIRL?
NO.  STAY BACK.
I-- PLEASE DON'T.
- YOU ARE NOT
A CREDIBLE EXISTENCE.
YOUR SOUL HAS BEEN
CONSUMED BY A DENIZEN
WHICH MEANS YOU
ARE NOW DEAD.
- ( gasps )
- YOU ARE NOTHING BUT A TORCH.
JUST A SHELL OF
THE HUMAN BEING YOU ONCE WERE.
- Junko:
I'M DEAD? NO.
IF THAT WERE TRUE,
I WOULDN'T BE STANDING HERE.
NO.
SOMEONE, PLEASE?
SAVE ME.  MOM, I--
- ( gate opens )
- JUNKO?
( gasps )
- ( door unlocks )
- YES, IT'S ME.
- WELCOME HOME.
( sighs )
- THAT HUMAN'S REACTION...
IT WAS RATHER BIZARRE.
- Alastor: YES.
THOUGH I DOUBT IT HAS
ANYTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
HUMANS ARE INCAPABLE
OF DETECTING
THE POSSESSION OF TORCHES.
- THAT'S TRUE.
THANKFULLY,
I WAS PREPARED THIS TIME.
THE TORCH HAD
A FAIR AMOUNT
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE
LEFT OVER.
AS A RESULT,
I WAS ABLE TO LEARN
MORE ABOUT ITS LIFE.
- Alastor:
YOU MUST USE THAT INFORMATION
TO MIMIC THE TORCH.
OTHERWISE THE HUMANS
WILL BEGIN TO SUSPECT YOU.
I KNOW YOU WOULD
PREFER NOT TO.
- I SIMPLY DON'T FEEL
THAT IT'S NECESSARY.
I AM ONLY STAYING
UNTIL THE DENIZEN
IS DESTROYED.
SHOULDN'T BE LONG.
THE ONLY REASON I'M HERE
IS TO FURTHER
MY INVESTIGATION.
NOTHING MORE.
THE FAMILY'S COMMON ROOM.
MIGHT BE CLUES HERE.
WEDNESDAY'S NEWSPAPER.
IF I SKIM THE LAST FEW DAYS,
I MIGHT FIND SOMETHING.
WHERE'S TODAY'S?
- I'M ABOUT TO START DINNER,
HONEY.
ANY REQUESTS?
- WHERE IS TODAY'S?
- HUH?
- THE NEWSPAPER.
WHERE IS IT?
- UH...
IT'S ON TOP OF
THE CABINET.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO WITH IT?
- READ.
- UH...
JUNKO, YOU FORGOT YOUR CAKE.
- Shana:
I DON'T WANT IT.
- ( sighs )
- AH HA.
- Alastor: HMM.
"AN AMERICAN CITIZEN
WHO WENT MISSING
IN NEW YORK 10 YEARS AGO
WAS RECENTLY FOUND
IN JOUSHI PARK
IN YOSEGI CITY."
- THIS MAN,
DO YOU THINK HE'S
THE TORCH WE SAW YESTERDAY?
- Alastor:
YES.
IT IS TROUBLESOME
THAT SUCH A WORN OUT TORCH
IS ATTRACTING SO MUCH
ATTENTION FROM THE HUMANS.
- Newswoman: THE AMERICAN
WHO WAS FOUND IN JOUSHI PARK
IS CURRENTLY MAKING HIS WAY
INTO THE YOSEGI POLICE STATION.
A MALE MODEL WHO WENT
MISSING 10 YEARS AGO.
THE MAN WAS FOUND IN
THE SAME CLOTHES HE WAS WEARING
WHEN HIS DISAPPEARANCE
WAS REPORTED.
THE MAN CLAIMS HE HAS
NO MEMORY OF THE LAST 10 YEARS,
AND THEREFORE HAS NO IDEA
HOW HE MADE IT TO JAPAN.
- Shana: THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
THE WORK OF A DENIZEN.
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
- Alastor: HMM.
THE MAN, NOW A TORCH,
WAS FOUND IN THE SAME ATTIRE
HE WAS WEARING 10 YEARS AGO.
MOST TORCHES DO NOT HAVE
ENOUGH POWER OF EXISTENCE
TO LAST A DECADE.
AND THE GUILTY DENIZEN
WOULD HAVE FLED LONG AGO
TO AVOID RETRIBUTION
FROM FLAME HAZE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
MOST DENIZEN FEAR US.
BUT THIS ONE SEEMS DEFIANT.
SO I GET THE FEELING...
IT'S STILL SOMEWHERE
IN THIS CITY.
- WELCOME HOME.
- YOU LOOK TROUBLED, DEAR.
JUNKO GIVING YOU
A HARD TIME?
- SHE SPOKE TO ME TODAY.
THAT'S BETTER, RIGHT?
THINGS WILL BE FINE AGAIN
ONCE WE TALK ABOUT IT.
- I HOPE SO.
- Alastor:
THE DENIZEN MUST BE WEAK
SINCE WE CANNOT
SENSE ITS PRESENCE.
WHY WOULD IT STAY HERE
FOR 10 YEARS
WHEN IT'S IN CONSTANT DANGER
OF BEING ATTACKED BY FLAME HAZE?
- AND EVEN MORE IMPORTANT,
IF THAT'S THE CASE,
WHY ARE THERE SO FEW
TORCHES HERE?
- Alastor: GOOD POINT.
WE SEARCHED ALL DAY AND
WE ONLY CAME ACROSS ONE.
- JUNKO OGAMI
IS OUR ONLY CLUE.
WE MUST FIND OUT WHEN
AND WHERE SHE MET THIS
DENIZEN.
- ( knocks on door )
- Junko's mom: JUNKO, DINNER.
- IF THERE HAD BEEN
SIGNIFICANT CHANGES
IN HER BEHAVIOR,
HER PARENTS
WOULD HAVE NOTICED.
- Junko's mom:
PLEASE, COME DOWN AND JOIN US.
- Alastor: THIS IS YOUR
CHANCE TO QUESTION THEM.
LIKE IT OR NOT,
YOU MUST MIMIC THE TORCH
FOR THE SAKE OF
OUR INVESTIGATION.
- FINE.
- ( chatter on TV )
- ( gasps )
THAT IS JUNKO'S FATHER.
- HAVE A SEAT, HON.
THAT'S USUALLY WHERE
YOUR MOM SITS.
DON'T YOU WANT
TO SEE THE TV?
- NO.
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, SIR.
- IF YOU SAY SO.
- ( remote beeping )
- Shana: INTERACTING WITH
HUMANS CAN BE SO TEDIOUS.
HAVE YOU NOTICED ANY CHANGE
IN MY BEHAVIOR LATELY?
- UH...
UH...
- I SURE HOPE
THE TWO OF YOU ARE HUNGRY.
- ( chuckles )
YOU KNOW I AM.
BEEN LOOKING FORWARD
TO THIS ALL DAY.
- ( TV shuts off )
- LOOK, JUNKO,
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET
ABOUT WHAT MOM SAID TO YOU.
BUT CAN YOU HONESTLY
BLAME HER?
- UM?
UHH...
- IT'S JUST THAT SHE...
WAS... YOU KNOW--
SHE WAS SHAKEN
BY WHAT SHE SAW.
AND SHE KIND OF PANICKED.
THIS BOY,
HAMAGUCHI, WAS IT?
HE SHOULD KNOW BETTER.
YOUR MOM WAS
PRETTY UPSET ABOUT IT,
AND SHE REACTED THE WAY
ANY PARENT WOULD HAVE.
JUNKO, HON,
ARE YOU LISTENING?
- NOTHING ELSE
HAS HAPPENED RECENTLY?
- OKAY.
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING?
- UH, WHERE'S THE NEWSPAPER?
- OH, I'LL GRAB YOU ONE.
- Junko's mom:
THANK YOU, JUNKO.
- HAVE YOU NOTICED
ANYTHING ELSE
ABOUT MY BEHAVIOR?
DO I SEEM TO
STARE OFF INTO SPACE?
ARE YOU STARTING TO HAVE
DIFFICULTY RECALLING
MEMORIES OF ME?
- UH--
- Both: WHAT?
- Alastor: HOW MANY TIMES
MUST I REMIND YOU
TO MIMIC THE TORCH?
YOU MUST ASSUME
THEIR PERSONALITY
AN UTILIZE THEIR CONNECTIONS.
YOUR QUESTIONING OF THE PARENTS
WAS SO STILTED,
YOU NEARLY BLEW OUR COVER.
- I LIKE TO GET
TO THE POINT.
THEY DIDN'T OFFER
ANY USEFUL INFORMATION.
- Alastor:
ACCORDING TO THE PARENTS,
THE TORCH SEEMED
PERFECTLY NORMAL.
- THEY DIDN'T NOTICE
ANY BIZARRE BEHAVIOR
OR CHANGE IN HER DEMEANOR.
THE ONLY INCIDENT
WAS AN ARGUMENT
SHE HAD WITH HER MOTHER
THREE DAYS AGO.
THERE IS THE BOY...
YUKIO HAMAGUCHI.
HE'S A CLASSMATE
OF JUNKO'S.
DO YOU THINK HE COULD
BE INVOLVED?
- Alastor: POSSIBLY.
LET'S GO TO THE SCHOOL TOMORROW
AND QUESTION HIM.
- ( footsteps )
- WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
- Alastor:
SHE IS STILL UPSET
ABOUT THE FIGHT SHE HAD
WITH HER DAUGHTER.
- WELL...
SHE'LL FORGET SOON ENOUGH.
ONCE I LEAVE YOSEGI CITY,
IT WILL BE AS THOUGH
JUNKO NEVER EVEN EXISTED.
SHE WILL JUST BE GONE.
AND HER MOTHER WILL FORGET
THAT SHE EVER
HAD A DAUGHTER.
- ( words silent )
- ( kids chattering )
- Shana: SHE WAS A HIGH SCHOOL
SECOND YEAR,
CLASS THREE.
( sighs )
- HEY, WHAT'S UP, JUNKO?
- THERE SHE IS.
- HOW YOU FEELING, LOVER GIRL?
- Shana: SO ANNOYING.
- YOU SNUCK OFF
WITHOUT SPILLING THE BEANS
AND NOW WE'RE DYING TO KNOW.
- YEAH.  WE WANT
ALL THE DETAILS.
- LET US LIVE
VICARIOUSLY THROUGH YOU.
- UH-- WHAT?
- COME ON.
DON'T PLAY STUPID.
- YOU WENT OUT
WITH HAMAGUCHI, RIGHT?
- SECRETS DON'T MAKE FRIENDS,
YOU KNOW.
- THEY'RE ASKING ABOUT
YUKIO HAMAGUCHI.
I WISH THEY WOULD
POINT HIM OUT.
I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN HIM AND JUNKO.
- IT'S JUST THAT SHE...
WAS, YOU KNOW--
SHE WAS SHAKEN
BY WHAT SHE SAW,
AND SHE KIND OF PANICKED.
- Shana: WHAT COULD HAVE
AFFECTED HER MOTHER LIKE THAT?
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT.
WHERE IS HAMAGUCHI?
- OH, YOU CAN'T BE
WITHOUT HIM, CAN YOU?
- JEEZ, YOU ARE
ONE LUCKY LADY.
- I'M SO JEALOUS.
- Shana: THESE GIRLS ARE
GETTING ON MY NERVES.
- Hamaguchi: MORNING.
- WELL, WELL.
SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
( gasps )
IS THAT HIM?
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- MORNING, DUDE.
- IT IS.
HAMAGUCHI.
- OH.  MORNING, JUNKO.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- WOW.  CHECK IT.
HE TOTALLY DIGS HER.
- HE LOOKS LIKE
HE WANTS TO KISS HER, HUH?
- I'M SO JEALOUS!
- I HAVE SUDDENLY
FALLEN QUITE ILL.
I MUST LEAVE.  PLEASE INFORM
THE INSTRUCTOR FOR ME.
- All: HUH?
- YOU'VE GROWN CLOSE TO
JUNKO OGAMI
OVER THE PAST FEW DAYS,
CORRECT?
- HUH?
- I NEED TO ASK YOU
SOME QUESTIONS IN PRIVATE.
- UH-- CAN'T IT WAIT?
- UH, JUNKO!
- HEY! YOU'RE SKIPPING CLASS?
- SO JEALOUS!
- WHAT HAS GOTTEN INTO YOU?!
- HEY!
- HUH?
( panting )
DID WE HAVE TO DITCH SCHOOL?
- APOLOGIES, BUT YES,
IT WAS NECESSARY.
- HUH?
WHY ARE YOU TALKING FUNNY?
- Shana: I REFUSE.
I WILL NOT MIMIC THE TORCH
JUST TO QUESTION HIM.
DESCRIBE WHAT'S TRANSPIRED
OVER THE PAST FEW DAYS.
- UH, DID YOU GET REAMED
BY YOUR PARENTS?
UH...
IS YOUR MOM STILL MAD?
- UH--
( sighs )
Shana: I NEED HIM
TO ANSWER QUESTIONS,
NOT ASK THEM.
- WHO KNEW WE'D GET CAUGHT.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
I GUESS IT COULD
HAVE BEEN WORSE, HUH?
I MEAN, AT LEAST THAT WAS
ALL WE WERE DOING, YOU KNOW?
SHE HAD TO WALK THROUGH
JOUSHI PARK.
BUSTED ON OUR FIRST OFFENSE.
( chuckles )
- Shana: HE MUST BE REFERRING
TO THE ACTIVITY
JUNKO'S FATHER MENTIONED.
WHATEVER IT WAS,
THIS BOY MAKES IT
SOUND HARMLESS.
I WONDER WHAT
THEY WERE UP TO.
- I'M SORRY YOU GOT
IN A FIGHT WITH YOUR PARENTS.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
- Shana: SO THE FIGHT
WITH HER MOTHER
WAS A RESULT OF THAT THING
SHE WAS DOING WITH HIM
THREE DAYS AGO.
( gasps )
JOUSHI PARK.
- HUH?
- OF COURSE.
- Newswoman: THE AMERICAN,
WHO WAS FOUND IN JOUSHI PARK
IS CURRENTLY MAKING HIS WAY
INTO THE YOSEGI POLICE STATION.
- IF YOU WANT TO GO,
I'LL TAKE YOU.
- FINALLY, A CONNECTION.
IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT I'LL TAKE IT.
- HEY, EARTH TO JUNKO.
- UH, SORRY.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU WERE SPACING OUT AGAIN.
- AGAIN?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- OH, I'M SORRY.
- NO, I'M NOT ANGRY.
I'M ASKING YOU.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
I SPACED OUT?
- YOU REMEMBER,
AT THE PARK?
YOU EXCUSED YOURSELF
TO GO TO THE LADIES ROOM.
I WAITED OUTSIDE
FOR AWHILE,
BUT YOU NEVER MADE IT BACK.
I WAS WORRIED
YOU GOT LOST,
SO I WENT LOOKING FOR YOU.
THAT'S WHEN I FOUND YOU
SPACING OUT IN FRONT OF
THE LAKE.
AT FIRST I WALKED
RIGHT PAST YOU.
I DIDN'T EVEN
REALIZE YOU WERE THERE.
- Shana: HE WALKED PAST HER
WITHOUT REALIZING SHE WAS THERE.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE MOMENT
SHE BECAME A TORCH.
THREE DAYS AGO,
JUNKO OGAMI BECAME A TORCH
WHEN A DENIZEN
CONSUMED HER SOUL
AT JOUSHI PARK.
( gasps )
- JUNKO, ARE YOU
FEELING ALL RIGHT?
- WALK ME THROUGH WHAT HAPPENED
AT JOUSHI PARK THAT DAY.
WHY WERE WE THERE?
WHAT WERE WE DOING?
EVERYTHING.
- UH...
- Alastor:
THE DENIZEN MUST HAVE
MADE CONTACT WITH
YUKIO HAMAGUCHI
AND JUNKO OGAMI
IN JOUSHI PARK.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
HOWEVER, THERE IS ONE THING
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW COME IT ONLY
ATTACKED HER?
WHY NOT KILL BOTH?
- Alastor: HOPEFULLY,
WE WILL COME ONE STEP CLOSER
TO SOLVING THAT MYSTERY
WHEN WE VISIT JOUSHI PARK
TOMORROW.
- Junko's mom:
WELCOME HOME.
I BOUGHT CAKE.
- EXCUSE ME?
- YOUR OTHER ONE
GOT CRUSHED,
SO I BOUGHT YOU ANOTHER.
- MMM!
- NO MATTER HOW OLD YOU GET,
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
MY LITTLE GIRL, JUNKO.
EVERY TIME YOU EAT,
EVER SINCE YOU WERE A BABY,
YOU END UP WITH FOOD
ON YOUR FACE.
- I HAVEN'T CHANGED?
- NOT MUCH.
I REMEMBER YOU USED TO
CRAWL INTO MY BED AT NIGHT
WHENEVER YOU WERE SCARED.
NOW THAT YOU'RE OLDER,
YOU STAY IN YOUR OWN BED.
BUT YOU'RE STILL
SCARED OF YOUR SHADOW.
WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE THOUGH,
IT DIDN'T MATTER.
WHETHER IT WAS HEAVY RAIN
OR THUNDER,
OR SOMETHING
ON TV SCARED YOU,
YOU'D RUN STRAIGHT
FOR MY BEDROOM.
- Shana: IT IS DIFFICULT
TO LISTEN TO HER MOTHER
REMINISCE LIKE THIS.
THE POOR WOMAN HAS NO IDEA
THAT HER DAUGHTER
IS DEAD.
- AND AFTER YOUR
BROTHER LEFT HOME,
YOU DID THE SAME THING
WHEN YOU FELT LONELY.
- REALLY?
SO I WOULD HIDE
IN YOUR BEDROOM
LIKE WHEN I GOT SCARED?
- HMM.
WELL, NOT EXACTLY.
IT'S NOT THAT
YOU WERE HIDING.
- WHAT WAS I DOING?
- YOU WERE LONELY.
YOU WANTED TO BE
CLOSE TO SOMEONE
BECAUSE NO ONE EVER...
WANTS TO FEEL THAT WAY.
- Shana: THIS WOMAN
WILL BE FREED
FROM HER LONELINESS SOON.
EVENTUALLY, HER MEMORIES
OF JUNKO WILL BEGIN TO FADE
UNTIL THERE ARE NONE LEFT.
THAT IS THE FATE
OF A TORCH.
- Junko's mom: HERE.
I HOPE YOU LIKE IT.
UNFORTUNATELY,
I COULDN'T FIND
ONE OF THE BEADS.
SO I'M AFRAID
IT ISN'T PERFECT.
IN ITS PLACE,
I USED THE GEM
FROM THAT RING YOU GAVE ME
YEARS AGO.
I KNOW IT'S ONLY PLASTIC,
BUT IT'S ALWAYS
BEEN PRECIOUS TO ME.
- ( gasps )
- ( Junko gasps )
( sighs )
( crying )
- I'M SO SORRY.
- ( chuckles )
Shana:
JUNKO WAS NOT UPSET.
SHE WAS CAREFREE.
I FORGIVE YOU, MOTHER.
- ( sighs )
THANK YOU, JUNKO.
- FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE COMING TO THIS WORLD,
I HAVE CAUSED
A SMILE TOO.
NOT ONLY AS THE TORCH
WHO'S PLACE I'VE TAKEN,
BUT AS A FLAME HAZE.
- Junko: I KNOW.
NEXT TIME, I'LL ASK HAMAGUCHI
TO COME WITH ME.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )