That's horrible...
You can't help it.
One person can't handle this alone.
But she knew that and came here anyway.
No, this isn't right, it's too much for her...
If she gives up, it's over.
But, you have the power to change this destiny.
All this tragedy, all this destruction,
you can change it, if you want.
The power to do so lies within you.
I can change it?
Even someone like me can do something to help?
Can I really change how this ends?
Of course, you can.
Just make a contract with me, and become a Magical Girl!
That was a crazy dream...
Good morning, Dad.
Oh, good morning, Madoka.
Mom up yet?
Tatsuya's waking her up.
He might need some help, though.
Okay.
Mama, mama!
Wake up, wake up!
C'mon, mama!
Mama, mama!
Rise and shine!!
Urghhhhhhhh!!
......What the...?
Mama woke up, yay!
What's happening in your world?
Well, Hitomi got another love letter.
It's the second one this month.
Huh, if he can't say to her face, he's not worth it.
How's Kazuko doing?
I think her new boyfriend's working out.
She can't seem to talk about
anything else during homeroom.
This week's their three months
anniversary, so I guess that's the record.
Oh I hope they can make it.
They're at a critical stage in their relationship.
They are?
If it's not the real thing,
this is usually when it starts to fall apart.
But if they made it this far,
they should be okay for another year.
Oh...
I look fabulous.
I wonder which ribbon I should wear.
Really?
It's not too flashy?
There's no such thing as too flashy, hon.
A woman can't afford to get
teased 'cause she looks sloppy.
Hah, perfect!
Your secret admirers are gonna get all wobbly and knees.
I don't have secret admirers.
But you should dress and behave like you do.
That's the secret every pretty girl should know.
Hehe..
Ah...
Uh-oh!
Yay, safe!
Now be good, and eat it all up, okay?
Okay!
Hey honey, some more coffee?
Uh...
I better not.
All right!
I'm off to work, everyone.
Have a good day, honey.
Bye, mama.
Hey, you're gonna be late if you don't hurry.
Oh yeah.
See you later!
Have a great day!
Good morning, guys!
Good morning.
What took you so long, Madoka?
Look at you with your cute ribbons.
You think so?
They're not too flashy?
I think they look lovely.
My mom said that if a boy can't say he loves
you to your face, he's not worth your time.
Your mom is way cool, Madoka!
I mean she's smart, gorgeous and successful.
If only I could make up my mind as easily as that.
If only everyone could have your problems.
You know, she is right.
I wish someone would send me a love letter some time.
It'd be nice to get one.
Ah, now I get it.
You want to be as beautiful and
popular as Hitomi, don't ya?
I bet that's why you're wearing
those ribbons to change your image.
That's not true!
My mom picked these out and...
You tricked your mom to tell you the
secret to being popular, didn't you?
I'm not gonna let that happen!
Ha!
No!
No, stop it!
You're just too cute!
I'm not gonna let you be popular with the boys.
You're mine, Madoka!
Mine, mine, mine.
Ahem.
I have a very important issue to discuss today.
So eyes front, ears open!
The correct way to fry an egg is sunny side up or down?
Come on, Nakazawa. I don't have all day.
I... I gue... uh...
You can fry either way, can't you?
Yes, precisely.
You can fry either way!
Therefore, go through without saying that you should never
judge a women's beauty by the way she fries her eggs.
Remember, girls, do not associate with men who
refuse to eat eggs that's been fried sunny side down.
I guess it didn't work out.
But what gave you that idea?
And you boys, better make sure you don't grow up to be men who
complain about how the damn eggs are cooked, understand?!
Well, now that that's out of the way,
let's give a big warm welcome to our new classmate!
Uh, maybe that should've come first?
Come in, Miss Akemi.
Don't be shy!
Wow!
Wow, she's super gorgeous.
Huh?
No way!
It couldn't be!
Why don't you tell the class
a little bit about yourself?
I'm Homura Akemi.
It's nice to meet you.
Uh...
Um...
Uh, Miss Akemi?
What school did you go to before coming to this one?
I went to a private Catholic school in Tokyo.
Were you in a club?
How about sports?
Were you on any teams?
No, not really.
Your hair is really beautiful!
What kind of shampoo do you like to use?
There's something awfully mysterious
about that girl, don't you think?
Hey, Madoka, do you know that girl?
I could've sworn to you she was glaring
at you when she was in front of the class.
Well, I'm not really sure...
I'm sorry.
I think today's been a little stressful for me.
I'm not feeling very well.
May I please go to the Nurse's Office?
Ah, sure.
If you want, I can take you over there.
Good idea!
Can I come too?
Please don't trouble yourselves.
I'll ask the Nurse's Aide to take me.
Huh?
Miss Madoka Kaname.
You are the Nurse's Aide for this class, are you not?
Huh?
Um, well...
I uh...
Would you please come with me?
To the Nurse's Office.
Um, I...was...
H-How did you know I was the Nurse's Aide for the class?
Ms Saotome told me that you were.
Oh, right, of course she did.
By the way, the Nurse's Office is over there.
This way, right?
Huh?
Uh, yeah, that's right.
But, um...
So anyway, how do you know your way there?
I mean you're new here and all.
Um...Miss, um...Akemi?
Call me Homura.
Oh, Homura.
What is it?
Uh, nothing. It's just that...you have an unusual name.
But not in a bad way or anything,
I was just thinking how it sounded cool...
for a first name, I mean.
Madoka Kaname, do you treasure
the life you currently live?
And do you consider your family
and your friends precious?
Oh, well, I uh...
Of course I do.
I mean I-I do.
My family and my friends, I love them very
much and yes they're very precious to me.
Do you mean it?
Absolutely.
I couldn't lie about that!
Good.
Because if that's the truth, then you wouldn't try
changing the life you have or the person you are.
Otherwise, you'd lose everything you love.
Huh?
Don't change.
Stay as you are, Madoka Kaname.
Stay as you are, forever.
Wow...
She breaks the record of every school in this city?!
I can't believe you can jump that high!
She said what?!
It doesn't make any sense, does it?
When I was thinking she was this awesome
girl but it turns out she is a total psycho!
Ah! I hope she doesn't think acting
like a weird transfer student is cool.
That's so MOE? It makes me sick!
This has to be misunderstanding.
Are you positive you've never met her before?
Hmm...
I guess the sensible answer will be "yes."
Okay, what do you mean by sensible?
Either you met her or you didn't?
Well, it's like...
You're gonna think I'm weird but I
first met her in a dream or something.
Hahahaha... That's awesome!
An anime character in you's popping out, too!
This is really bugging me!
I got it all figured out.
You guys knew each other in the past life and the fate is
reached across time and space to bring you back together again.
In your dream, what happened when you met her?
That's the thing. I can't really
remember what happened in it.
All I know is that was really strange and spooky.
If you want my opinion, I think it's entirely
possibly you met Miss Akemi somewhere before.
Huh?!
You might not remember meeting her,
but your subconscious certainly took note of it.
When you were having that dream,
your subconscious simply brought up the image of her.
Seriously?
That's the heck of coincidence, don't you think?
Uh, perhaps.
Uh-oh, look how late it's gotten.
Excuse me, but I really should be going now.
Is it Piano today or classical dance?
Tea Ceremony lessons today.
Even though our Exams are coming up,
my mother still wants me to continue taking them.
Yeah, there's another reason to
be glad I wasn't born a rich girl.
We should get going too.
Madoka, you wanna hit the music store on the way home?
Okay.
Something for Kyosuke again?
Yeah, maybe.
Have fun shopping!
Later!
Is that you?
Help me...
Homura?
Get away from that creature.
B-But he's really hurt.
Leave him alone.
Why are you trying to hurt him?
This doesn't concern you.
But he was calling me!
I could hear him calling my name!
He was asking me to help him!
Really?
Over here, Madoka!
Sayaka!
Why is this happening now?
Now she's attacking you on cosplay?
What's her problem?
And what's that thing you're carrying?
Looks like a stuffed animal. Is it alive?
I don't know.
I don't know why this is
happening, but we have to save him!
Where'd the exit go?
Where are we?
I don't like this place.
Everything keeps changing!
Oh, crap!
What the heck's going on?!
There's something over there!
Is this some kinda joke, right?
I'm stuck in a bad dream, but I am dreaming, right?
Right, Madoka?!
What's happening?
I don't know.
That was close, wasn't it?
But don't worry, you're safe now.
Thank goodness.
You rescued Kyubey for me.
I'm very grateful.
He's a dear friend of mine and I was so worried.
He called out to me.
I could hear his voice inside my head.
Ahh, I see.
I can tell by your uniforms that you
both go to Mitakihara Middle School.
Are you 8th graders?
Who are you?
Oh, that's right.
Maybe I should introduce myself.
Actually, it's going to have to wait a bit.
Please excuse me.
I have to wrap this up first.
Wow, amazing!
We're back!
The witch managed to escape.
If you wanna finish it off, you'd better go after it.
I won't mind if you take it this time.
But I still have work to do here.
You don't understand, do you?
I'm telling you I'm willing to overlook this.
Honestly, don't you think it would be
best if we didn't do this right now?
Thank you, Mami!
You're a lifesaver!
I'm not the one you should be thanking.
They saved you.
I was just passing by.
Thank you very much!
My name is Kyubey.
Were you the one who was calling for help?
That's right, Madoka Kaname,
And Sayaka Miki.
Wow, hang on a sec.
How do you know our names?
I came here because I have a favor to ask of you both.
Huh?
What do you mean?
I want you to make contracts
with me,and become magical girls!
I will grant each of you one wish, any wish you desire.
Huh?
For reals?
Anything at all?
Anything at all.
I can grant the most impossible of miracles!
That would be truly wonderful.
Huh?!
Come on, that's mean!
Bye bye!
Help me!
Huh?
Madoka, help me!
What?!
Please...help me!
Huh?
Hello?
Who are you?
Help me..!
Where are you?
Um, do I know you?
Help me!