Oh, are you here to see Kyosuke?
Uh-huh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
His examination got moved up.
He's in Physical Therapy right now.
Oh, okay then.
Thank you.
She comes to see him a lot, doesn't she?
It's good she does.
He's a difficult case.
He needs encouragement and I think she gives him that.
He was a musical prodigy before the accident, wasn't he?
The violin?
Yes.
But even if he figures out how to walk again,
his fingers will never recover enough to play.
Why did it have to be Kyosuke?
I can move my fingers as much as I want.
But they don't do anything special.
Why couldn't it have been me instead of Kyosuke?
If I used my wish to heal Kyosuke,
how would he feel about it?
Would he just say "thanks?"
Nothing else just "thanks" and that's it?
Or am I hoping for something more to happen?
What am I thinking?
I'm horrible.
Uh-oh.
Hold still.
Oh, got it.
Madoka.
Fast move, kid, you're gonna be late for school.
Mm-hm.
Huh?
Why's Sis crying?
What's wrong? Don't you like your breakfast?
Yeah... it tastes good...
Really good...
I'm alive...
And your cooking... it tastes so good, Dad...
I was all like "Jeez, Yuka!" really!
I mean, after all that she still doesn't get it.
And then, oh and then, she gets all weepy and goes
"What did I say something weird again?"
I wanted to laugh so hard but I
held it in for as long as I could.
...Me, too!
I couldn't, so I just sat there choking back laughs.
That's so funny.
Ahem.
Let's use the prime age for
childbirth in women as an example.
Sure, it's based on certain medical
facts, but counting backwards from there,
to determine whether a woman's
suitable for marriage is incorrect!
Women over the age of 30 are
absolutely suitable for marriage.
And there's no scientific proof to the contrary.
Now, having said that, and hoping it's
absorbed by your fertile little minds,
we should use the present progressive tense here-
It sort of...feels like we're
in another country, doesn't it?
Even though nothing's changed, our school is the same,
our class is the same, Hitomi, nothing's changed.
But I feel like I'm surrounded by strangers.
No one else knows, that's why.
No one knows about witches, or Mami.
It's like everyone else is living in
a totally different world than us.
You and me, we are the only ones who know about
all the stuff that's been happening lately.
Sayaka...
Everything changed a long time ago, didn't it?
And the two of us should've figured
that out sooner, don't you think?
So after all this, what we've seen,
do you still wanna be a magical girl?
Yeah, I thought so.
Hey, I understand.
I-I know it's unfair.
I know it's selfish to back out now.
But I...
I can't...
Just thinking about the way she died...
Even now, it gets so hard to breathe...
I'm scared...
I don't want that...!
Mami...really was the nicest person.
But in order for us to understand what it takes,
the kind of courage it takes to fight,
she can't...
Hey, Kyubey.
What's gonna happen around here now?
Since Mami's gone, is there someone else around
who's gonna protect everyone from the witches?
This town's been Mami's for a long time.
Once the other magical girls find
out she's gone, they'll come.
I'm sure someone will arrive soon to pick up the hunt.
And then what?
All they're gonna care about is finding Grief Seeds.
Just like that transfer student.
It's true.
Most magical girls hunt for their own benefit,
and it's normal to wanna be paid for your work.
But Mami was a rare breed.
But then...
You don't have the right to judge their actions though.
Only magical girls have that right.
They share the same destiny after all.
Phew.
I understand what you're thinking.
It's a shame, but I can't force you, can I?
Good-bye then.
I'm off to search for other girls,
who have a greater need to make a contract with me.
I'm sorry, Kyubey.
No, I apologize for getting you mixed up in all this.
We weren't together for very long, but it was fun.
Thank you, Madoka.
I'm sorry...
for being so weak.,,
Homura...
You shouldn't blame yourself for what happened.
It couldn't be helped.
Huh?
No one can criticize you for anything.
I mean that.
No one.
I won't allow it.
So then, have you accepted my warning?
Uh-huh...
I keep thinking, if only I'd listened to you before...
If you had, it wouldn't have changed Mami Tomoe's fate.
I was able to change yours though.
That's good.
So at least I saved one person.
I'm glad about that.
Um, you know, Homura.
I get the feeling you're a veteran at this too.
I mean like Mami, but different.
Perhaps.
I can't deny it.
And I guess...
you've seen lots of people die horribly, haven't you?
I have.
How many?
I gave up counting long ago.
And her place...is it just gonna stay like that?
Most likely.
She didn't really have any family to speak of.
And it'll be a very long time
before she's reported missing.
Then, no one's gonna notice Mami's dead?
It can't be helped.
If you die in a labyrinth, your body stays there.
That means in this world,
she'll be considered a missing person forever.
It's a fate all magical girls come accord to,
eventually.
That's awful!
She was all alone, she fought to protect everyone...
And now you're saying no one will know she's gone..?
That's horrible!
It's a condition of the contract we
make, in exchange for our powers.
We're not protectors.
We fight for the sake of our wishes,
and this is how we pay for them.
If we die and no one remembers us,
I guess that's just the way it is.
I'll remember her.
I'll never forget her,
never.
I promise!
I see.
Mami Tomoe is lucky.
She'd be happy to hear that.
How I envy her.
I won't forget you either!
I swear I'll never forget you, Homura,
and how you saved us yesterday!
I'm always gonna remember you!
Homura?
You're too kind.
Huh?
Remember this, and take it to heart.
Kindness sometimes leads to even greater tragedy.
What are you listening to?
The Girl With the Flaxen Hair.
Oh, that's Debussy.
It's a beautiful song!
Uh, you know what?
It's kinda funny but...
I don't think people really see me as the type
who listens to stuff like classical music.
And whenever I can name a piece correctly,
seriously you should see their faces.
It's like they're impressed
that I know about that stuff.
Everything I know about it is 'cause of you.
Seriously though, I would never
even listen to classical music ever,
if it wasn't for you, you know.
Hey, Sayaka...
Huh?
Yeah?
Cut it out.
Stop torturing me already.
Why do you keep coming here?
You think I like listening to this music?
It's like you're trying to hurt me.
But, Kyosuke, I-I thought you loved music.
I don't wanna hear this crap anymore!
What's the point if I can't play!
All I can do is listen!
I...
I just...
I just, ah!
I can't move it...
I can't even feel the pain anymore!
My hand's useless.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm sure someday, somehow...
Don't give up hope!
Don't figure something now!
But they came and told me to give up.
They said I'll never play again.
The doctor told me, he said the
current medicine can't help anymore.
My hand is never gonna move right again.
Unless magic and miracles suddenly become real.
But they are!
Miracles, magic, they are real!
Huh?
Is that Hitomi?
Hey, Hitomi!
I thought you were in a practice today.
Where're you...huh?
Hitomi!
Hey, Hitomi come on!
Ah, good evening, Madoka. How are you?
Huh? What happened to you?
Do you know where you are, where you're going?
Where am I going?
I'm going somewhere wonderful, that's where.
Hitomi...
Oh, yes.
And you simply must come with!
Yes. You'll see.
It'll be so wonderful!
I'm worthless.
It's true.
A failure.
I couldn't even keep this little factory's
door open long enough to turn a profit.
There's no room for a person like me in today's world.
I'm...obsolete.
Pay attention, Madoka.
These bottles look the same, but this one is dangerous.
Never mix the two of these together, understand?
We could all get really sick and die if you do.
Do not mix them up.
No, stop it!
Don't do that!
This is a sacred ceremony.
We can't have you interrupting it.
But those chemicals're really dangerous!
If you mix them together, everyone here could die!
Yes, and we're all going to go on a wonderful journey,
to a magnificent new world.
Don't you see what an amazing opportunity this is?
We can finally get rid of
these bodies that hold us back.
Oh, Madoka, in a little while you'll understand too.
Let go of me!
What do I do?
No...
Go away...
No.
Someone help me!
Help me!
Sayaka?!
You're so going down!
Yeah, sorry I'm late.
I guess I cut it too darn close, didn't I?
Sayaka...
Your clothes.
Huh? Oh, hahaha.
Well, uh, you could say I sort of had a change of heart.
Don't worry. I'll be okay!
I mean I did pretty good for
my first time out, didn't I?
Yeah, but...
How could you..?!
Huh.
You're late, Transfer Student.
I didn't expect you to show up.
I came all this way 'cause I heard old Mami bought it.
So, why don't you tell me something?
What's the deal, huh?
This isn't anything like what you said.
Sorry, but this territory has been
taken over by another magical girl.
She made a contract with me a little while ago.
What the hell?!
That pisses me off!
I mean, I couldn't live with myself
if I just handed prime territory
like this over to some rookie.
That'd be crazy.
What are you going to do, Kyoko?
Simple.
I'll just...
put her dumb rookie ass out of commission.
Permanently.
I'm excited about this.
Seriously.
From now on, I'll promise that
I - Magical Girl Sayaka
- will do my best to protect
the peace of Mitakihara City!
There's no way I'll ever regret it.
Now that I think about it,
I really didn't understand anything back then.
What it meant to pray for a
miracle, or the price of one.
Sayaka, I need to talk.
Sorry, not now.
We'll talk later.
When I was talking with Homura,
it felt like we could be friends.
I wonder why she and Mami didn't get along?
Huh? It's like what that woman had on her neck!
What should I do?
This can't be happening!
I have to call Homura.
Oh, but I can't!
I don't have her cell number.
I wonder if this...
is my punishment.
For being...
a coward...
and a liar.
I guess this...
is what I deserve.