Shutting off the pain's pretty
easy once you know how to do it.
This way I'll never lose another fight.
You can have it.
That's what you're here for, isn't it?
Watch it.
I don't wanna owe you anything.
We're even now.
Got it?
Let's get out of here, Madoka.
Sayaka...
Ah...
Sorry...
I'm still a little tired...
Take it easy.
I got you.
That idiot!
Sayaka...
You can't fight like that.
You're lying if you say it doesn't hurt.
It hurts just watching you.
Just because you can't feel the pain,
doesn't mean it's okay to hurt yourself.
I don't have the knack for it.
[If] I don't fight like that, I can't win.
Even if you fight like that and win every
battle, it's not good for you.
Can't you see that?
Then what is "good for me?"
Ah..?
I've been turned into a monster.
How can anything ever be good for me again?
Sayaka...
All I can do now is kill witches.
That's my new purpose in life.
I'm useless otherwise.
I'm just a walking corpse
pretending like I'm still alive.
Who's gonna help me now?
The way I am, who'd want to?
Why you even think about it?
But I wanna help.
I just don't know what to do to make you happy again.
Then why don't you fight for a change?
Wanna know what Kyubey told me?
You've got more potential than anyone.
You could beat any witch [with] no problem
and you wouldn't even suffer like I do.
But I...
I just...
If you really wanna help me, you should try
putting yourself in my shoes for a change.
But you can't.
Of course not.
You won't even give up your
humanity out of pity for a friend!
It's not that I want!
It's just...
You can do anything but you won't.
You just sit there 'cause it's okay
if I'm the one who's suffering.
Don't act like you care.
It's obvious you don't.
Sayaka, wait!
Don't follow me.
Uh...
I'm so stupid...!
How could I say those things..?
I'm so hopelessly stupid...
Walpurgisnacht is supposed to appear in this area.
Oh, yeah?
What makes you so sure?
Statistics.
Huh.
I've never heard about Walpurgisnacht
showing up here before.
You mind telling me where you
got these statistics of yours?
Huh...
Look, we don't have to trust each
other and be all BFF's or anything,
but do you think you could maybe
give me an idea of what's going on?
I was wondering the exact same thing,
Homura Akemi.
You've got some balls showing your face around here!
Oh, my.
Perhaps I'm not welcome here after all.
And after coming all this way,
just to give you some very important information.
What?
Sayaka Miki is deteriorating fast.
And not only because she used too much magic,
there's a curse growing inside her now.
And whose fault do you think that is, huh?
I don't doubt she'll be causing you quite a bit trouble,
even before Walpurgisnacht arrives.
You'd best be on your guard.
What do you mean trouble?
Come on, let's have it.
You might wanna ask her about that instead of me.
I'm sure you already know what
I'm talking about, Homura Akemi.
I thought so.
I'm curious, how did you learn
about all these interesting things?
Enlighten me.
I think I've heard enough from you today.
Get out.
Great.
You're just gonna let him go?
There's no point trying to kill that creature.
Take my word.
What's up with Sayaka Miki?
What kind of trouble do you think
that fuzzball was talking about?
Her Soul Gem is tainted.
And if it's not purified soon,
there won't be anything anyone can do to save her.
Now, the auxiliary verb "must" means that
something or other has to be done,
but "have to" has a slightly different vibe.
For example...
Why did I let her go?
I should've gone after her.
Wait...
I don't think I've ever seen you
walking home this way before.
How come?
Did you just move or something?
Actually, my house is in the exact opposite direction.
Okay...
Then, why are you walking this way?
Kyosuke...
There's something I've been wanting to tell you.
She hasn't come home?
Since yesterday?
Oh...
Yes, um...
I understand.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Sayaka...
I've gotta find her!
Ahhhhh!
Why can't you understand?
You don't have the luxury to fool around.
You should only hunt witches.
Shut up!
I don't need your advice.
Your Soul Gem is at its limit.
You need to purify it now.
Use this.
What is this?
What are you up to?
Don't be stupid.
You're in no position to question my help.
Or, do you just hate the idea of it?
I'm gonna be a different kind of magical girl.
That's what I decided.
I'm not gonna screw anyone over
or take anyone for granted.
And I won't associate with anyone who does!
I don't need anyone's thanks.
I'll be the only magical girl around
who doesn't use her magic for herself.
Well, then.
You're going to die.
So what?
If I'm gonna die, it's gonna be
when I can't kill witches anymore.
No one's gonna need me anyway, right?
I'm okay with that.
The world doesn't need a magical girl,
she can't even kill a witch.
Why are you doing this to yourself?
Why won't you trust me?
Can you see I just wanna help you?
Why don't I trust you?
Maybe it's 'cause I can tell what you really are.
Maybe I know you're lying.
You look like someone who's given up on everything.
When you talk, you use empty words.
In fact, you're doing it now.
You say you wanna help me,
but I know that's not what you're really thinking.
You're not fooling anyone.
Uh-uh.
Do you realize that you're just
making Madoka suffer more and more?
Madoka?
This has nothing to do with her.
You're wrong.
Everything has to do with her.
You're sharp.
Yes.
You're right about me.
I don't give a damn if you live or die.
I don't care.
I just don't want Madoka to see you like
this, as you destroy yourself.
If you don't let me help you now,
you're going to die, either way.
You see, if you make her suffer anymore,
then I will...
kill you...
right here right now, Sayaka Miki.
Hurry!
Go on! Get out of here!
What are you, crazy?!
What happened to saving her?
You remember that?!
Let me go.
Oh, I get it.
If I keep holding onto you like this,
you can't use that funky technique of yours, can ya?
Ah!
Dammit!
No way, man, you can't let the
dumb slut make excuses like that.
You gotta make her hand all her cash over.
Dumb bitches.
You only get their hands on some coins and
they blow it all on stupid shit for reals.
Seriously, gee.
Can't treat 'em like they got any brains.
That's for sure.
Treat 'em like the dumbass bitches they are.
My hoe's so dumb, she freakin loves it like that.
I just tell her, "I'll bust your shit!"
She shuts right up!
You let up on 'em and they're all like
"I wanna get married."
You can't be soft, man.
Can't be soft, heh.
I'm all like, you think a shit-for-brains hoe
like you's gonna be making it as much in ten years?
That body ain't gonna last forever, you know!
And then you dump 'em, and they get all "why me".
You know, who's gonna dumping hoes, Sho, man, Sho.
Now that motherfu...
I wanna know more about your girl.
What the...?
I wanna know about the girl you
guys were just talking about.
Tell me more about her.
You're like in middle school, kid.
You should be home in bed.
Your girlfriend, I bet she loves you and tries
really hard to make you happy, doesn't she?
I bet you know she does, don't you?
And instead of saying thanks,
you sit there calling her a bitch.
Then dump her when she gets old.
Yo, you know this kid?
No...
Hey, is this world even worth protecting?
What have I been fighting for all this time?
Answer me,
right now.
Come one, tell me.
Or else...
Where are you, Sayaka?
I bet you're upset with me too, aren't you?
If I was, would you change Sayaka back?
I can't.
It's beyond my power to do so.
Hey.
Remember when you told me I could become a
really powerful magical girl if I wanted?
Was that for real?
Really powerful doesn't even begin to describe it.
Your power would be almost limitless.
You'd be the strongest magical girl in this world.
If I made a contract, would Sayaka still
have chosen to become a magical girl?
Sayaka was responsible for her own wish.
You had absolutely nothing to do with her decision.
Why am I the powerful one?
I have no idea.
The truth is your potential is on a scale that,
theoretically anyway, shouldn't even be possible.
I want someone to come explain it as much as you do.
Really?
If you release your power,
you could do more than miracles.
You could very well twist the
fabric of the universe itself.
Why you've been selected to have
this power over anyone else,
I can't even begin to guess the reason.
You know...
I never thought there was anything
all that special about me.
I always thought, I'd just stumble through life,
not really amounting to anything much,
never being able to help anyone
or be of any use at all.
It was really frustrating and I felt all alone.
But I figured there wasn't anything I could do about it.
But the reality is different, isn't it?
Madoka, if you wished it,
you could even become the god of this world.
If that's true,
would I be able to do stuff
that even you can't do, Kyubey?
Like what?
Like if I went ahead and made a contract with you,
could I turn Sayaka back to normal?
That would be like child's play for you.
Would that be worth trading your soul for?
Would you like to?
Yes.
For Sayaka, I would.
I'll do it.
I wanna be...
a magical...
Uh..?!
What did you do?
You didn't have to kill him!
You idiot.
Why do you do that?
Why do you always sacrifice yourself like that?
Huh?
Calling yourself useless, and meaningless...
Stop treating yourself like you don't matter!
Why don't you ever think about
all the people who love you?!
Stop being such a fool!
There are so many people who would be sad if you died.
Why can't you understand that?!
What about the people who are
trying hard to protect you?!
Homura...
Ah...
I get the feeling we've done this before...
I-Is that true?
Have the two of us met before?
I-I can't...
Sorry...
I have to go find Sayaka now.
Wait,
Sayaka Miki is...
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Madoka!
You knew there was no point in doing that.
You don't learn, do you?
I have plenty of spares, you know.
But don't make me use them up for no reason.
It's such a waste.
You know, that's the second time you've killed me.
But this time, you showed me what your technique is.
That was time manipulation, wasn't it?
I thought so.
I've suspected for a while,
but I wasn't sure.
You're not from this timeline, are you?
I know what you really are,
and I know what you're planning.
Uh-huh.
That's why you've been trying so hard to spoil my plans.
Do you wanna change Madoka Kaname's fate that badly?
I do.
And I'm gonna do whatever it takes to stop you,
Kyubey.
Or should I say,
"Incubator?"
Finally, I found ya.
So how much longer are you gonna
do this stubborn thing, huh?
I'm sorry if I caused you any trouble.
Seriously?
Doesn't sound like you at all.
Hmm...
Yeah, you're right.
I guess I just don't care anymore.
I can't remember...what I thought was so important,
or what was worth protecting, you know.
It's all blank now, doesn't make sense anymore.
Hey, come on.
Ah..!?
Balance means good and bad have
to zero themselves out, right?
That's what you said...
or something like it.
I think I understand what you mean now.
The good thing is,
I did save a few people.
But the bad thing is,
I got angrier,
and my heart filled up with envy and hate.
It got so bad.
I even hurt my best friend.
Sayaka!
Your Soul Gem!
For all the happiness you wish for someone,
someone else gets cursed with equal misery.
That's how it works for magical girls,
and that's how it is for me.
I was stupid...
so stupid.
Sayakaaaa!!
On this planet, you call females who
have yet to become adults "girls."
It makes sense then,
that since you'll eventually become witches,
you should be called "magical girls."
I know this sounds kinda crazy but...
The thing is, we don't know she can be saved yet or not.
So there's still hope for that,
I'm not gonna give up.
I'd never allow that to happen.
Hey, you.