You tricked us, didn't you?
Not necessarily.
I did make it perfectly clear.
I wanted you to become a magical girls.
I just didn't explain the exact form
you'd be taking to do, that is all.
Why wouldn't you tell us something like that?
Because you never asked.
Besides, even if you never found out,
it wouldn't bother you one bit.
In fact, Mami never found out, even at the end.
You humans don't even realize you have souls.
They're not something you can
physically feel inside you.
Your bodies are such fragile containers.
Just a cluster of neurons,
organs and the circulatory system.
It's an amazing construction.
But once your bodies stop functioning,
your soul disappears.
To keep that from happening,
I put your soul into a physical form.
It makes the soul easier to protect,
and easier to keep track of.
That way, you can battle witches
and not have to worry about it.
Well, nobody asked you to do that, did they?
You still don't understand
the dangers of combat, do you?
Ugh...
Let's say you've been impaled by a spear.
Do you know how much stimulus would
register in your pain receptors?
Argh!
That is what it would feel like.
One strike, and you're completely incapacitated.
The reason you stayed standing
during the fight with Kyoko
is because you were spared the
pain your body was experiencing.
And that was possible because your soul
and body weren't directly connected.
You were able to survive that
fight because of your modification.
Once you get used to it,
you figure out how to block out all the pain.
There's a downside though.
Your reaction time suffers.
So, I don't recommend it.
How could you do this to us?
Why?
You did accept the destiny of fighting witches,
provided I grant one wish for you.
That wish has come true, hasn't it?
Stand.
Bow.
You knew about this, didn't you?
How come you didn't tell us about it before?
Would you believe me if I did?
I tried telling others before, but no one ever does.
But why would Kyubey do something so cruel to us?
Because it doesn't think what it did was cruel.
That creature doesn't understand human values.
A soul's a fair exchange for granting someone's wish.
That's what it thinks anyway.
But there's nothing fair about it!
What he did to her isn't right!
All Sayaka wanted was to help someone she
loves, to help him get better again.
An agreement is still an agreement.
It made the impossible possible, didn't it?
That boy would've never gotten better,
no matter what,
even if Sayaka Miki spent the rest
of her life taking care of him.
The truth is, a miracle like that
is worth more than a life of human.
That's the price it sells them for.
Does that mean Sayaka can't go back to her normal life?
I already told you once.
You really should forget about Sayaka Miki.
But she's my friend and she saved my life!
If Sayaka hadn't become a magical girl,
Hitomi and I would both be dead right now.
Don't confuse gratitude with responsibility.
There's nothing you can do to save her now.
And if you're trying to repay
her to ease your guilt, don't.
That's arrogant thinking, and you should stop it.
Why do you always act so cold?
Well...
Maybe I behave this way because I'm not human anymore.
How could I ever face Kyosuke again?
Now that I've been turned into this thing.
Huh?
What happened to us sucks.
I bet you regret ever making that contract, don't ya?
But you know, me, I think I'm okay with it.
I mean, I can do whatever I want with my powers.
Who cares about the details?
I don't really think it's a deal breaker, you know.
You think you got what you pay for, huh?
Oh, yeah, I did.
That's a great way to look at it.
Think about it. If you live for
yourself, you only got yourself to blame.
So I can't really blame anyone
else and I don't have any regrets.
See?
If you look at it that way,
you won't beat yourself up about it.
You brought me all the way out here, just to talk?
Uh-huh.
Got a lot to talk about.
You want one?
Ugh...
I see you wasting food like that again, I will kill you.
Uh...
Wanna know where we are?
It's my dad's church.
He was an honest man and way too nice.
He's the kind of guy who'd read
the papers and start tearing up,
'cause he couldn't figure out how to make things better.
He thought religion hadn't adapted enough.
He wanted something new,
something that made sense in today's world.
So one day, he started preaching stuff to
the congregation that wasn't in the Bible.
People got upset, stopped coming to his sermons.
The church kicked him out, and after that,
well, nobody cared about what he had to say.
Heh, go figure, right?
I mean, from the outside,
I bet he looked like he was trying to start a cult.
Didn't matter if what he said was
right or even if it made any sense.
Everyone treated him like he was a psycho.
It got so bad for my family that there were
lots of times where we didn't have any food.
I couldn't understand it.
My dad wasn't doing or saying anything wrong.
It was just different from what
everyone was used to hearing, is all.
If people would've just calmed down,
gave him five minutes and really
listened to what he had to say,
they would've seen he was right.
Yeah, but...
in the end, nobody did.
I got mad, like really pissed off.
I hated that nobody gave my dad a chance and
tried to understand what he was talking about.
Then, Kyubey showed up and I made my wish.
I wanted everyone to listen to my dad and
take the stuff he was saying seriously.
The next morning, they came back.
The church was packed with so many people.
Everyday, there was more and more
people coming to hear my dad preach.
And me, I started doing the magical girl thing.
I figured, no matter how awesome my dad's sermons were,
they weren't gonna take care
of the witches any time soon.
It was my job, so like an idiot,
I threw myself at hunting witches full time.
We were gonna save the world together,
him doing it out in the open and me in the shadows.
And one day, my dad found out
about what was really going on.
Man, I'll never forget it.
When he realized everyone was there,
not because of what he was preaching,
but because of my magic, he totally lost it.
And then he called me, his own daughter,
an evil witch who corrupted his flock.
Heh, isn't that hilarious?
I'm the one out every night hunting
real witches and he calls me a witch!
After that, my dad had a breakdown.
He got really depressed.
He was drinking a lot and then he went crazy.
He killed my family and then he committed
suicide, leaving me behind...
alone.
The thing I wished for destroyed my whole family.
I brought all this suffering down on my family
'cause I made a wish for my dad,
without knowing what he really wanted.
So right then and there,
I promised myself I'd never use
magic to help anyone else ever again.
This power is mine, and I'll use it for me and me alone.
Miracles aren't free, you know?
If you wished for something good to happen,
a whole lot of bad stuff's gonna happen, too.
I guess that's how the world stays in balance.
Good, bad, everything zeroes out.
Why are you telling me all this stuff for?
'Cause I want you to stop
caring and do what you wanna do.
Hey, you got what you pay for, didn't ya?
I'm a little confused.
You just got done telling me all
about how you're in this for yourself.
Why are you worrying about me all of a sudden?
'Cause you and me,
we both made the same mistake, didn't we?
You gotta stop feeling the way you do
'cause it'll only bring you more pain.
You already paid your dues,
way more than what you got for 'em.
Know what I think?
You take what you got and figure
out how to get something out of it.
Kinda like how you do?
Exactly how I do.
Look, I figured out how things
work and wanna save you some grief.
I can't stand seeing you go through this.
I had the wrong idea about you from the beginning.
I'm sorry about that.
So, forgive me.
But still, I don't have any regrets
about using my wish for someone else.
And I've decided that from now
on, I'm not gonna regret anything,
ever again.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Honestly, I don't think I paid
too big a price for what I got.
I think magic can be used for great things,
depending on how you use it.
Which reminds me...
those apples.
How did you get them, huh?
Mind telling me where you got the money for them?
...Ugh...
Hmpf.
Yeah, thought so.
In that case, I can't eat those apples.
I'm not gonna have any part of them.
You idiot!
We're magical girls!
There's no one like us!
Nobody can do what we do!
I'll do things my way,
and fight my own battles.
If you don't like it, then you can come
find me and try to kill me if you want.
I won't hate you for it.
But I won't lose to you either.
Tsk...
Good morning, Sayaka!
Wait up!
Ah...
Good morning, Sayaka. How are you?
H-hey.
Good morning.
Why didn't you come to school yesterday?
Oh, um, I felt a little sick, is all.
But, Sayaka...
Mm.
Hey, I got an idea.
How about we go and...
Oh...
I didn't know Kyosuke was out of the hospital.
Hey, Kyosuke.
You're okay to be back here?
Yeah.
If I stayed home,
it wouldn't help get my legs back in shape.
I'm hoping to get off these crutches
and be walking on my own by next week.
I'm glad Kyosuke is doing better.
Mm-hm.
You haven't talked him yet, have you?
Why don't you go over and say hi to him?
No, it's okay.
Maybe later.
Uh...
Okay...
Whatcha wanna talk about?
I wanna talk about love.
I'll explain it.
There's something I haven't told you or Madoka.
But I can't stay silent any longer.
Huh?
Oh, okay.
For a long time now, I...
I've always liked Kyosuke Kamijo.
And I'm in love with him.
O-oh, you are, huh?
I-I never would've guessed, Hitomi.
Th-That's awesome.
I hope Kyosuke knows just how lucky he is.
You've known Kyosuke for a while.
Weren't you friends since childhood?
Oh, yeah, sort of.
We hang out together every now and then.
And it's nothing more than that?
I've got long and hard about this.
I can't lie to myself any longer.
So, how about you?
I need to know, can you face your
true feelings for him, Sayaka?
Uh, true feelings?
What do you mean?
I take my friendship with you very seriously.
And I don't wanna get into a situation where
you think I'm stealing him away from you.
I wanna respect the relationship you have with Kyosuke,
because you've known him a lot longer than I have.
That's why if you like him,
you have a right to go after him before I do.
Hitomi...
I'm going to tell Kyosuke how
I feel after school tomorrow.
That gives you one day to decide.
Will you confess your true feelings to him or won't you?
Think about what you want so you
don't have any regrets later.
I...
I just...I...
Madoka...
Is it okay if I come along?
I won't get in the way.
I just don't want you to be all alone.
Can I come?
Why?
Why are you always so nice to me?
I don't deserve having a friend like you...
What?
I started to have...second thoughts today.
Uh...
I thought...what if I hadn't saved Hitomi.
It was just for a second, but still...
I guess I'm not a hero after all.
What would Mami think if she was still here?
I'm going to lose Kyosuke to Hitomi.
And there's nothing I can do about it now.
Because I'm...
I'm already dead!
I'm a zombie...!
I can't ask him to hold me if I'm like this!
I can't ever ask him to kiss me..!
I feel better now...
I'm sorry...
You don't have to be....
I'm okay.
Thanks for listening, Madoka.
Come on, let's go!
We've got some witches that need beating down!
Right.
You are the last person I'd
expect to just sit and watch.
Tonight's the real deal.
She's fighting a witch, not a familiar.
If she beats it, she'll get a Grief Seed.
So at least she's fighting for something.
I'm surprised you give up your prey so
easy, just to help her out.
What the hell is she doing?
She's gonna get herself killed!
Hahh!
Sayaka!
Geez.
I can't watch this any more.
Hang out here, okay?
Let me show you a couple of basic moves.
Hey!
I can do this alone.
Get out of my way.
Sayaka!
Ha ha ha...
What's going on with her?!
Ha ha ha.
It's true!
I can block out the pain!
Ha ha ha!
I don't feel any pain anymore!
Stop...
Please...
stop...
I'm gonna be a different kind of magical girl.
That's what I decided.
I don't need anyone's thanks.
I'll be the only magical girl around
who doesn't use her magic for herself.
I was stupid...
so stupid.
Hey, dummy.
How much long are you gonna stay inside?
Can you come out for a sec?
I wanna talk.
It's cool.
I feel fine.
You don't have to worry about a thing.