You're sure you can grant any wish, for real?
You don't have to worry.
I can grant yours without any problem.
So...
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Do it.
There...
Accept it.
This is your destiny.
Oh, excuse me.
That was terribly rude.
What's up, Hitomi?
Didn't you get enough sleep?
I didn't.
I was up really late talking to the police
and getting checked out at the hospital.
Really?
What happened?
Well, apparently,
I was sleepwalking or some such thing...
Oh, but there were several
others who had the same symptoms.
And when we all woke up and found
ourselves in a strange place together.
Oh, what's up with that?
The doctor said we most likely
suffered a mass hallucination.
So, after school today,
I have to go back to the hospital for more tests.
Ohh, it's such a bother.
After going through that,
you shouldn't have come to school today.
I couldn't do that.
If I stayed home, then everyone would think I was sick.
I don't want my parents to worry
about me more than they already are.
Spoken like a true honored student.
That's our girl!
I haven't felt this good in a long time.
I feel awesome!
Sayaka.
Aren't you scared?
Huh?
Well, I guess I am a little.
I mean it wasn't too hard to beat that witch.
I gotta admit, it was kinda easy.
Yeah, but if I start thinking about
how I could've lost you and Hitomi,
man, that scares me way more.
So, how do I really feel?
I feel sort of, confident,
more at ease.
I kinda feel like I wanna congratulate myself, too.
Anyway, I'm excited about this, seriously.
From now on, I promise that
I - Magical Girl Sayaka
- will do my best to protect
the peace of Mitakihara City!
Are you sure you don't have any regrets?
I guess...
if I had to pick one,
it'd be that I waited as long as I did.
But in the end, I did it anyway,
so I should've made up my mind sooner.
If I was a magical girl when Mami
fought that witch, I could've helped.
Then maybe she'd still be alive.
Maybe...
Hey, you're not thinking what I
think you're thinking, are you?
I...
Maybe I should have...
Don't you start going "could have, should have."
Hindsight's twenty-twenty.
I feel like I was meant to be a magical girl.
So I shouldn't have dragged my feet
about her for as long as I did.
Sayaka...
I knew what I wanted more than anything else.
Never meant to have to risk my life fighting witches.
So what?
I would've wished for it anyway.
It took a long time to realize how much that wish meant.
So that's a little frustrating.
So, after all that, my point is don't feel guilty.
It's okay if you don't wanna be a magical girl, too.
Maybe you just weren't meant for it.
Anyway, I'd better get going, I'm gonna be late.
Do you have something important to do?
Yeah, sort of.
Really?
Why aren't they letting you go home yet?
I still have to finish the rehab for my legs.
So, I can't really do anything until I can walk again.
Plus, everyone's still wondering how
my hand healed as fast as it did.
They're concerned about it.
The doctors wanna run some more
tests on it to find out what that is.
How are you feeling now, Kyosuke?
I mean, do you have any pain anywhere?
No, I feel so good, it's scary.
I was thinking about it,
the accident almost seems like a bad dream now.
It's weird.
I wonder what I'm even doing in this bed.
It's just like you said, Sayaka.
It's a miracle.
Hm?
What's wrong?
The other day, I said some awful things.
I was really upset and it was wrong.
Forget about that stuff.
It's no big deal.
Your hand's working again.
You should be totally happy about that.
So, don't make that face.
Right...
I guess it still feels like a dream.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not surprised.
Oh, it's about time.
Hm?
Well, how about you and me go out for some fresh air?
Why are you taking me up to the roof?
Don't worry. You'll see.
What's going on?
We were going to have a party
when you got out of the hospital.
But we figured since your hand's all better.
I-Is that?
I know you told me to get rid of it, but...
I-I just couldn't throw it away.
Take it, Son.
Go on.
Play something.
You don't have to be afraid.
'Kay...
Huh...
So, that's what the new magical girl in town looks like.
You're not really going to
pick a fight with her, are you?
Sure, why not?
She won't know what hit her.
I promise.
Why? What's up?
You got a problem with that or something?
Not at all.
But it might not be as easy as you think.
There is another magical girl in the city after all.
Oh, really?
So, what's her story?
I'm not really sure about that.
Huh?
You gotta be kidding.
If she's a magical girl, then she had
to've made a contract with you, right?
You could say yes.
You could also say no.
She's an irregularity in this world.
And I have absolutely no idea what she's capable of.
Hmpf. Sounds good to me!
Gettin' kinda boring around here, anyway.
Gotta shake things up.
You know what I'm saying?
You wanted to talk?
Um...it's about Sayaka.
And well...
She might be stubborn, and...
...maybe a little hypersensitive too...
And maybe she kind of likes to argue a lot...
but she really is a wonderful person!
She's kind hearted and brave,
and she's always ready to help someone if they need it.
Those're fatal flaws for magical girls.
Oh...really?
A person becomes naïve if they're too kind.
Careless if they're too bold.
And no matter how hard you try to protect
others, there's no gratitude.
Those who can't comprehend such
things aren't fit to be magical girls.
That's the reason why Mami Tomoe lost her life.
Don't talk about her that way!
Anyway, Sayaka, she says she'll be okay on her own.
But then, when I think about Mami and how
the same thing could happen to her, I...
just...
I don't know what to do.
You're really worried about her, aren't you?
Mm-hm.
I am.
But I can't do anything to help her all by myself.
So I was hoping I could ask you to help her.
Please be friends with Sayaka.
And please don't fight with her like you did with Mami.
If everyone can work together,
then when you go out to fight witches,
it'll be a lot safer for everyone.
I don't make a habit of telling lies.
And I don't make promises that I can't keep.
Uh?
Therefore, you should forget about Sayaka Miki.
Why should I..?
She shouldn't have been allowed to make the contract.
I'm partly to blame for it.
I'll admit that.
I should have looked out for her, as I do for you.
Then she...
although I'm partly to blame, you must understand.
This is a mistake which she can neither
undo, nor recover from,
the same as how the dead can never return to life.
Once you become a magical girl,
there is no turning back.
When we decide to make a contract,
we give everything up in exchange for
one single wish.
But then, does that mean you've given up, Homura?
On all the other girls, even on yourself, for real?
Yes.
I won't make any excuses for myself.
No matter what sins I must bear,
I will continue my fight to the end.
If I'd wasted your time, I'm sorry.
Madoka?
Sayaka.
Are you going...?
Yep!
Time to patrol for wicked witches!
It's my duty.
Now that I'm an ally of justice.
Are you okay by yourself?
Oh, I'll be fine.
Hey, Mami worked alone, too.
And if she can do it, then so can I!
Um, I know...I don't have any powers,
and I guess I'll probably end
up just getting in your way,
But if...
if you don't mind having me around,
I'd like come with you.
At least as far as you can take me.
You're so stubborn.
Sorry,
it's a lot to ask,
but I figured I'd give it a shot.
No, I'm happy you did.
You feel that?
My hands are totally shaking.
They haven't stopped this whole time.
Isn't that pathetic?
Even though I'm a magical girl,
the thought of going alone's kinda scary.
Sayaka...
I want you to come.
It'd make me happy.
I already feel way braver now,
knowing you're gonna with me!
I could beat up 100 bad guys now!
But what if...
I'll keep you safe.
Just follow my leading, you'll be okay.
I promise.
Ready to go hunt some witches now,
just like we used to?
Mm-hm.
You know this is going to be dangerous, right?
Mm.
You know how I am.
If I went alone, I'd be reckless and get myself killed.
But if Madoka's there, I won't act stupid.
I think about what I'm doing, and be more focused.
You see?
Mm.
Well, as long as you've thought it through.
Kyubey...
This is it.
This labyrinth was probably the
creation of a familiar, not a witch.
I should still be careful though.
After all, I'm still new at this.
Keep your guard up.
Roger that.
Here it is!
What do we do?
I got it.
Hang on a sec.
What do you think you're doing?
Playing tag?
Uh, it's getting away!
What are you? Blind or something?
That is no witch, it's a familiar.
And you ain't gonna have any Grief Seeds on it.
Yeah, I know.
But if we leave it alone,
it's gonna go and kill someone!
Listen, Chick.
It's gotta eat 4 or 5 people
before it turns into a witch.
Then, when you kill it,
you're sure to get a Grief Seed out of the deal.
You don't wanna kill the goose before
it laid the golden eggs, Rookie?
What about the people it's gonna attack?
Seriously?
You're gonna let them get killed?!
You know what?
Hate to say it, but you've got this whole thing wrong.
Ever hear of something called the food chain?
Didn't they teach you it in school?
The witches go and eat weak humans.
And then we hunt them down and eat the witches.
It's the natural way of things.
The weak have to give up to the strong.
Oh, no...
Why you...
Oh, don't tell me...
You don't really believe in all that "saving
people" and "fighting for justice" crap, do you?
Come on now, you didn't buy that load of bull, did ya?
And what if I did, huh?!
Whatever.
Wanna stop that?
I don't like you're coming here
and acting like it's a game.
That pisses me off.
Sayaka!
Hmph! Rookie.
Go cool your head for a while.
You gotta be kidding.
The hit you took should've put you in
the hospital for at least three months.
Kyubey, is she okay?
She wished for someone to be healed when she
made her contract to become a magical girl.
So now, she has the power to heal fast.
Think you're so tough, don't you?
Mami's gone because of magical girls like you!
Okay.
That really pisses me off!
You know something?
You shouldn't talk to me like that.
I've been doing this thing way longer than you.
Shut up!
Gonna jump around all day,
or are you gonna fight back?
Sayaka!
It's too dangerous!
You don't get it when I explain it.
And trying to beat some sense
into you ain't really working.
Guess my only option is to kill ya!
I won't lose...
Not to you!
Why?
Why is this happening?
She's not a witch.
They're magical girls,
they shouldn't be fighting each other!
It can't be helped.
Neither of them is willing to back down.
Please, Kyubey...
Make them stop!
This is crazy!
There's nothing I can do.
However...
If you wanna stop them and you don't
mind using force, there is a way.
Only another magical girl could come between them now.
And you're more than qualified to become
one, if you really want to.
Game over!
I wish...
There's no need for that.
But Sayaka, you became a magical girl
so you can fight witches, didn't you?
She isn't a witch.
She's a magical girl just like you.
This just can't be right.
But...
No, Madoka.
Hey, Mami.
See that?
My wish has been granted.
There's no way I'll ever regret it.
And right now, this is the happiest moment of my life.
Are you nervous?
A little.
One mistake and it's goodbye me.
You've thought this through as
well, haven't you, Madoka?
I know how much you want to protect Sayaka.
I think it's good you're coming along with us.
That way, if we find ourselves in a bad
spot, you'll be a trump card.
But I...uh...
You don't have to decide now.
And I'm sure Sayaka will be against it.
But if you ever do decide on something to wish for,
remember, I will always be ready to grant it for you.
Okay...
That's right.
If I make a contract with him, then...