I'm Mami Tomoe.
I'm a 9th grader at Mitakihara Middle School.
And...
once I made a contract with
Kyubey, I became a magical girl.
I had another weird dream.
Huh?
Good morning, Madoka.
Ah!
Hehehe...
Madoka.
You got in pretty late last night, didn't you?
I got invited over to a friend's house.
I don't wanna start cracking down
on you with curfews and stuff.
Next time, let us know where you are before dinner.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
Cool apartment.
I live alone, so make yourselves at home.
Although as far as refreshments go, I don't have much.
Wow, Mami.
This is so delicious!
Mm, super delicious!
Thank you.
Since Kyubey chose the two of you, that means
you're both involved in this, like it or not.
I though it might be good if we had a talk.
Mm-hm.
Go ahead, ask us anything you want.
Sayaka, you've got it wrong.
Ah, pretty!
It's called a Soul Gem.
When Kyubey chooses a girl,
it's created when she makes a contract with him.
It's the source of our magic,
and it also proves that we're magical girls.
What's this contract?
I will grant each of you one wish, any wish you desire.
Huh?
For reals?
Anything at all?
Anything at all.
I can grant the most impossible of miracles!
Oh, we could wish for treasure.
Or eternal youth?
Or 108-course banquet?
Maybe that last one's a bit much.
In exchange for that wish, your Soul Gem is created.
But if you have a Soul Gem,
it would be your duty to fight witches.
Witches?
Um, hey Mom?
Hm?
This might sound silly but,
um, if someone could grand any
wish you wanted using magic,
what would you wish for?
I'd wish for those two trustees to
get kicked right out of the company.
Hehehe...
Come to think of it,
There's the CEO.
He's too old to keep up the pace like he used
to, so maybe I'd wish for him to retire.
Thing is, he hasn't named a successor yet.
What would you do if you became the new CEO?
Ah, how would I go about it?
If I can get enough support from the Sales Department,
the Planning Committee and General Affairs,
that leaves old Baldy in the Accounting.
Interesting...
Mom, your eyes are scary.
What is a witch anyway?
Are they different from magical girls?
If magical girls are said to be born from wishes,
then witches are creatures born from curses.
Magical girls bring hope to the
world, witches bring despair.
And since they're invisible to humans,
they are that much more insidious.
Anxiety and mistrust, rage and hatred...
They sow the seeds of disaster all over the world.
Suicides that can't be explained and murders without motive,
a witch's curse is most likely the cause of such things.
It festers within a person,
and grows and grows until it consumes them.
If there're things like that out there,
how come people don't know about them?
A witch is careful about not letting humans see them.
They hide deep within the labyrinths they create.
You know that maze-like place you were in today?
That was a labyrinth.
Actually, you were both in a lot of danger.
If a human ever wanders into one,
they seldom make it out alive.
Is that what you do?
You fight these horrible creatures, Mami?
Yes, I risk my life.
That's why the two of you should
think carefully before you decide.
Kyubey chose you and offered a rare chance,
it's true you'll grant whatever wish you can think of.
But remember death is part of that deal.
Huh?
Oh, now I'm stressed.
I know it's a tough decision.
But maybe if you went on a few witch hunts with
me, it'll help you decide.
Huh?!
See for yourselves what it's like to fight a witch.
Think about the offer a little longer.
Think long and hard.
Ask yourselves, is this something you want so badly
that is worth putting your life in danger for?
Good morning!
Oh, good morning!
Hey! Urgh...
Good morning, Sayaka!
Ugh.
You look ill.
Is something the matter?
Look like we're the only ones who can see him, huh?
I guess so.
What are you...?
Nah... it's nothing.
Well, let's go!
Huh?
Excuse me.
What's going on between you?
Why do you keep staring at each other?
Huh? Oh... Uh...
It's...just...
I can't believe it!
Just by looking at each other,
you know what the other's thinking?
Oh, for two people to become
that intimate after one night?
What did you do after I left yesterday?
I can't believe she's going there.
Well, actually...
lots of things happened but...
That's enough! You can't be serious!
You're both girls!
Girls can't love girls!
Girls can't love girls...
Hey, wait!
You forgot your bag!
Huh, what's wrong with her?
Hitomi's acting just like you today.
What the heck is that supposed to mean?!
Are you sure this is okay?
I mean tagging along to school and everything.
That transfer student, you know the new girl in class?
Is she the same as you? A magical girl?
She is.
There's no doubt.
And she is a very powerful one, too.
Then she is a good guy.
I mean if she fights withes and stuff like you, right?
But then, why would she do something like attack Madoka?
It was me she was after.
I think she was trying to keep me from
making a contract with a new magical girl.
Yeah, but...
If we're fighting the same enemy,
wouldn't it be better if there were more of us?
No, not necessarily.
It's more common for magical girls to fight each other.
Really?
But how come?
When you defeat a witch, you acquire certain rewards.
That's why, depending on the situation, magical
girls will fight, and the winner gets the reward.
Okay, hold up, so the reason the weird transfer
student was staring at Madoka yesterday,
was 'cause she knew Kyubey was trying to contact her?
Most likely, yes.
Anyway, the form of the verb we're talking
about is called the 'active voice.'
For the ones taking notes, that's when the subject
to the sentence is doing something to the object.
Now, the flip side of that is the 'passive voice.'
That's when the subject to the sentence is
having something done to it by the object.
Take a sentence, "he likes me," the subject is 'he.'
And since he is the one doing
something, the sentence is in the act...
Here.
Hey, Madoka.
You have any luck trying to figure
out what you're gonna wish for?
Uh-uh.
How about you?
I don't have a clue.
I'm totally stumped.
I've thought about it so much
my brain is starting to hurt.
I mean, there's a bunch of
stuff I wanna have or do, but...
Maybe it's the risk-your-life
part, maybe that's holding me back.
Yeah well, nothing I want's worth that
much, that's for sure.
Mm...
That's so odd.
Most girls accept my offer right away.
Then...
I guess we don't know any better, do we?
Really?
Do you think so?
Yep. We're blissfully ignorant.
Just think about it for a sec.
Have you ever wanted something so
bad, you'd trade your life for it?
There's tons of people out there,
with a lot less than we have,
who'd jump at a chance like this.
You see, we can't figure out what to wish for,
'cause we don't know what it's
like to want something that bad.
We're blissfully ignorant to any kind of suffering.
Why us?
Why did we get this chance?
Uh...
It's not fair, is it?
I get to have a wish, but you know,
there's other people out there,
who deserved it a lot more.
Sayaka...
Back for more, huh?
No.
I haven't come to fight.
I wanted to kill it,
before it made contact with Madoka Kaname.
It's too late for that now.
Well, now what?
Are you going to become a magical girl?
I'm, uh...
Yeah, right.
Like it's any of your business.
I warned you, remember?
Yes.
Very well then.
I hope my warnings aren't in vain.
Good bye.
H-Homura.
Um, wait!
I'd like to know what you wished
for when you became a magical girl.
Hitomi!
Oh, something private?
Well, uh...
I'm so jealous!
I guess it's true what they say how two's
company, and three's a crowd!
You got it all wrong, again...
Miss Akemi,
We're going for coffee after school, wanna come with us?
Not today.
I've got some stuff to do.
I'm sorry.
Aww.
Well, time to start Lesson One
of the Magical Girl Experience.
That's what I'd like to call it, anyway.
I hope you're ready.
I don't know if it'll make a difference but...
I brought this!
I mean it's better than not having anything, right?
Well, let's say I'm glad you're
going into it with that spirit.
How about you?
What'd you bring?
Huh?
Nothing...
Just this.
Ooh...
I-I sort of thought...it'd be good to
have some costume ideas just in case.
Ha ha ha...!
Huh?
Well, you certainly have the right spirit.
That's so awesome!
I can't top that!
Ha ha ha!
It senses the magic residuals
of the witch we saw yesterday.
When we hunt, we have to scout the city by foot.
Once your Soul Gem picks up a trail,
follow it until you find the witch.
Really?
That's it, huh?
What now?
Your Gem's not going any brighter.
That's because it's been a whole
day since the witch escaped.
The trail has almost faded away.
Then, if you'd gone after it right away last night...
I might have been able to finish it off.
But I would've had to leave the two of
you alone and I didn't wanna risk it.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Yep! You really are an ally of justice, Mami.
Not like that psycho.
What's her deal anyway?!
She really pisses me off!
Hey, Mami.
When you're tracking a witch,
do you look any place special for them?
Sometimes you'll find traces of
witches' auras about fatal car crashes.
So I check streets with heavy traffic.
Then the Red Light District,
where fights usually break out.
Also I check places people go to commit suicide.
Then I check the hospitals,
the worst place for a witch to hide.
It's unbearable to see them draining the life force
from a helpless person, who's already weak from illness.
It's picked up some powerful magic.
It's close.
There's no mistake.
It's here!
Look up there!
Ha!
A Witch's Kiss.
I knew it.
Is she dead?
She's okay.
She just fainted, is all.
Let's go!
You won't escape this time.
Whoa, look at that!
Oh, wow!
It's not much, I know.
But it'll help you fight off
anything that tries to attack.
Stay close to me once we're inside, okay?
'Kay!
Get back!
How about it?
Are the two of you scared?
Yeah, as if.
Keep going.
We're almost at the center of the labyrinth.
Look.
That is a witch.
Eww... Gross!
It's awful!
Are you really gonna fight it?
I'll be fine.
I could never lose.
Stay back! Don't move!
Oh, no!
Mami!
I'm okay.
I can't let myself look uncool in
front of my magical girls trainees!
Let's wrap this up.
Tiro Finale!
So, you won?
Awesome!
This is a Grief Seed.
It's a witch's egg.
An egg?
Witches will carry them sometimes.
If you're lucky you'll find one after a battle.
Don't worry. When they're like
that, they're perfectly safe.
In fact, they're valuable because of what they do.
The color of my Soul Gem looks staler
than it did last night, doesn't it?
It does.
But, if I do this with the Grief Seed...
See?
Wow! It cleared right up.
Uh-huh.
And the magic I used during the
fight has been restored, too.
Remember those rewards that I talked about?
This is it.
It should be good for at least one more use.
Take it!
I'm giving it to you.
Miss Homura Akemi.
Her again.
Hmm...
Maybe you're not the sharing-with-others type.
It was your kill.
So, keep the reward for yourself.
Fine.
If that's what you want, so be it.
Seriously!
She bugs the hell out of me!
But why can't we be friends with her?
She has to want to be friends, right?
What the...
Huh?
Where am I?
Ah! I... Oh, god!
No...
I just...
I jumped but I don't know why...
It's okay.
Don't worry. You're safe now.
See?
You were just having a nightmare, is all.
Well, I guess that's it.
Case closed, huh?
Mm-hm.
Hey, sorry but we sort of have a
couple of errands to run, so...
I just pretend to be cool.
When I'm scared or hurt, there is no one I can talk to.
All I can do is cry on my own.
It's not fun...
...being a magical girl.
I'm not afraid of anything anymore.
People really can't see him.
We can communicate like this,
just by thinking to each other.
You mean we already have magical powers?
For reals?
No, not yet.
I'm letting you communicate your thoughts through me.
But it's kind of a handy trick, don't you think?
It feels sort of...weird.
Why not?
That psycho chick who was trying to kill
you yesterday just transferred to our class.
You're sort of risking your life being here.
Actually, I think the school is the safest place for me.
Besides, Mami's here.
Mami's a 9th grader,
she's way over on the other side of school.
Don't worry, I can hear all of you perfectly.
She's not that far, so my telepathy can still reach her.
Oh, uh, um, good morning!
I promise I'll keep a close watch over you.
Besides, she doesn't seem like the
type who would attack you in public.
If you say so...
Ugh... Speak of the devil.
Don't worry, Madoka.
If she steps out of line and tries anything
funny, I'll punch her lights out.
Besides, Mami's got our back.
That's right.
I'm here, so everything will be fine.
Regardless of Sayaka and her punches.
What do you mean 'regardless?'
It's okay.
I wonder...
Is she really a bad person...?
I'm scared...
But...
It's still really hard for me
to figure out what I'd wish for.
It's not something I can put my finger on that easily.
But Mami tries so hard to save people.
She looks so amazing doing it, too.
If someone like me could do that,
go around helping people who're in trouble?
Well, I think that would be...
...truly wonderful.