Ray: Norman’s getting...
Shipped out?
Isabella: Yes.
It’s happening tomorrow.
( Emma wincing )
ray: So, then,
what happened to Emma?
Isabella: It was a clean break,
- so don’t worry.
- ( Children gasp )
Isabella: I guarantee
it’ll heal up perfectly
without a scar,
though it’ll take
a few months to do so.
I do hope that it’s healed
before your birthday, ray.
( Ray growls )
Isabella: And, Norman,
give me that bag later.
( Norman gasps )
Isabella: Now let’s
go back to the house.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
( Birds chirping )
Don: What are we supposed to do?
( Gilda moans )
Don: Norman’s
getting shipped out.
She took the rope.
Not to mention,
Emma can’t move.
Ray: Emma’s gonna
heal up in no time,
and the rope can be replaced!
The escape can happen.
it has to!
But norman’s our focus for now.
gilda: Out of all of us,
why was he picked to be shipped?
Ray: When she said
the situation changed,
she meant the next shipment.
It was about Norman.
Gilda: She even...
Got rid of sister krone.
Don: It seemed like everything
was normal this morning, right?
She was smiling and doing chores
like she usually does,
and now she’s gone,
and it’s all because of mom.
( Gasps )
( Gilda whimpers )
( Ray growls )
( Clock ticking )
Norman: Emma.
( Emma sighing )
( Gasps )
( Crying )
norman:
There’s no need to worry.
All she did was take the rope.
Emma: But that’s not the point.
Norman: You don’t
have to give up on this.
Your leg will heal.
emma: No, Norman!
We can’t let you get shipped!
Norman: You’ll succeed
in escaping.
Emma: You’re coming, too, okay?
You have to, ’cause we need you!
Norman: Thirsty?
I’ll get some water.
Emma: Norman!
( Footsteps receding )
( Door opens )
( Door closes )
( Crying )
( Clock ticking )
( Water flowing )
( Norman sighs )
( Gasping )
♪
Don: Ray, what about Norman?!
Ray: He’s going to escape,
no matter what!
( Don and gilda gasp )
( Ray growls )
( Gasps )
Don, gilda...
Let’s go.
( Both gasp )
( Both grunt )
( Door opens )
Ray: We’re getting Norman out.
( Emma grunts )
( Water flowing )
( Norman gasping )
( Faucet creaks )
( Sighs )
( Chuckles )
I’m back. Eh?
Ray.
Ray: The plan is...
Tomorrow you’ll escape
by yourself.
Emma: You won’t die,
not on our watch.
( Clock ticking )
Norman: Sorry, but...
I can’t.
- Both: You can!
- ( Norman grunts )
Ray: But to be more accurate,
- you’ll just pretend to do it.
- Norman: Huh?
Ray: You’ll disable
your tracking device,
fake an escape,
then hide in the area
’til emma’s healed up.
Emma: And on the day
of the escape,
you’ll run away with us.
Norman: Yeah, but,
even if it’s fake,
once I go,
security’ll get tighter.
Ray: Not a problem.
Based on the houses’s
caretaking policies,
security won’t increase much.
Norman: Caretaking policies?
ray: One,
to let us all grow freely.
Two, strict confidentiality.
the first is
for developing our brains.
A child that grows up freely
with rich emotions,
that’s the minimum requirement
for the product here.
Norman: So then,
point two means...
Ray: Yeah, the demons
stay out of sight.
If we fear them, our brains
won’t grow as planned,
so the worst they’ll do is
add more guards or caretakers,
and those things,
we can deal with. I know it!
norman: Even so,
if they end up making the wall
taller than it is now, how do
you plan on climbing over it?
Ray: You can make a ladder
while you’re hiding out
in the forest.
Norman: What if they
change the tracking device
to a more complex one?
Ray: If they implant new ones,
we’ll know where they are,
so we’ll take them out!
We can handle it!
( Norman sighs )
Ray: Don’t you get it?!
we’re telling you
that you don’t have to die!
I’ll supply your food and
keep you hidden, no matter what.
Tighter security
should be no problem!
And I still haven’t used
my trump card to outwit mom,
so stay alive! Just pretend
to run away, and then--
- Norman: I can’t.
- ( Ray gasps )
Norman: Sorry,
but it won’t work.
It’s not security. If I run,
you or Emma might end up
getting shipped in my place.
To have one of you
get killed instead of me,
I couldn’t bear it.
( Ray gasps )
Norman: They can have my life,
but I have no intention
of giving them anything else.
i’ll destroy
what mom’s been plotting
and make sure
the escape plan succeeds.
( Ray shuddering )
Norman: But thank you, really.
We should come up
with a new plan,
one that you guys
can execute after i’m gone.
Ray: You idiot.
Six years, that’s how long
i’ve planned all this!
Norman: Sorry.
( Ray gasps )
Damn it.
emma: Well,
ray could break his leg, too.
Both: Eh?
Emma: Smart, right?
You just break a few bones.
Ray: Emma, what are you...
Emma: I think, since my leg’s
in pretty bad shape,
it’s probably unlikely i’ll get
shipped out in norman’s place.
( Norman gasps )
Emma: ’member what we
heard at the gate?
We’re high-grade merchandise
and special, too.
when we go out,
we’ve gotta be in perfect form.
If someone were to take
his place, it’d be you,
but if you got hurt like me,
you wouldn’t
get shipped out right away.
( Ray laughs )
Good thinking, Emma!
- Let’s do it.
- Emma: Yeah?
ray: How about
we break my arm instead?
Emma: Great idea. Arm, it is!
Norman: Wait a second, guys.
There’s no proof
you won’t get shipped out
if you get hurt like that.
emma: Then,
we’ll make him catch a cold!
Ray: You think the demons won’t
wanna eat me if i’m sick, huh?
Norman: Uh...
emma: So you’ll
break your arm and get sick.
You sure you’re okay
with all that?
Ray: Yeah.
Emma: Why don’t we
make string telephones
so we can discuss plans
through them? ( Giggles )
Ray: Sure sounds fun.
Also, that way,
mom won’t hear us.
- Norman: Y-you guys--
- Emma: If that doesn’t work,
then i’ll think
of another plan!
I’ll do anything!
Norman: But why?
This plan’s just crazy,
isn’t it?
emma: Well,
I like it much better
than letting you die.
Remember what you said once?
"We’ll all flee
from here together."
so, if you’re not part
of all this, I won’t accept it!
Let’s live together, okay?
( Norman shuddering )
Yeah.
Ray: Catch.
( Norman gasps )
Ray: Use this thing
to disable your tracker.
Go hide in the forest.
Then you’ll climb the wall.
norman: And scout
before they increase security.
Ray: We’ve got
a new rope coming,
thanks to Don and gilda.
They’re using spare sheets
from the linen room.
Emma: So it’s done, then.
ray: Press it
against your left ear,
and hit the button.
That’ll disable
the tracking device.
If we use this thing,
mom won’t know.
Emma: Is it made
from camera parts?
Ray: It’s more than just that.
i used parts
from the rewards I got from mom
and disassembled them.
From the camera,
all I really wanted
was the strobe.
Norman: You’ve collected
these parts for six years,
just so mom
wouldn’t figure it out.
Emma: Amazing.
Ray: There’s no need
to be impressed about it.
I realized the houses’s secret
and had to do it,
and that’s that.
- Norman: Ray.
- Ray: Eh?
Norman: Something’s
been bothering me.
How’d you find out?
I know I asked you this before.
a normal kid
wouldn’t have realized it.
Ray: I’ve always known.
( Norman gasps )
Ray: I’ve just always known.
( Emma and Norman sigh )
ray: You know
what infantile amnesia is?
Emma: Uh-uh.
Ray: When most people
reach a certain age,
they don’t have any memories
from being a baby.
That’s infantile amnesia.
- ( Norman gasps )
- Ray: But, in some cases,
there are humans
who don’t forget everything.
Emma: Wait. You mean...
Ray: I still have...
memories
from inside of the womb.
- ( Both gasp )
- Ray: Some of my memories
didn’t match
with what i’d been told.
That’s how I knew.
my first memory
is being in a dark liquid.
I could hear a lullaby
from somewhere.
Emma: Do you remember a lot,
or is it hazy?
Ray: All of it’s in fragments,
but in high detail...
Demons’s faces
and how there were
other babies there.
They implanted the trackers,
and then we were divided
into batches of five.
Norman: Five?
Ray: After that,
I went through a tunnel
and was here.
Norman: The tunnel
being the gate?
- Ray: Yeah.
- Norman: Wait.
So past the gate
isn’t outside, but...
Ray: Headquarters.
( Norman gasps )
Ray: The headquarters and
the adjacent five plants.
those are
what make up this house.
emma: Then,
what krone said was true,
every last detail.
ray: The gate
can’t be an escape route.
( Emma sighs )
Ray: Beyond it,
things get rough.
there’s not
just a few guards out there.
It’s swarming with demons.
Emma: Isn’t that bad, though?
Ray: Not quite. Because of that,
the security is pretty thin.
Their main focus
will be on the gate,
so we won’t have to worry much.
Once emma’s leg is healed,
we’ll run.
Emma: Oh, I see.
Ray: We’ve got everything
worked out, Norman,
so tomorrow you’ll disappear.
( Sighs )
Norman: Understood.
( Insects chirping )
Isabella: Attention.
I have good news.
A foster family chose Norman.
I know it’s sudden, but he’ll
be leaving tomorrow night.
( Girl wails )
( Children murmuring )
- Boy: That soon?
- Boy 2: Congrats!
Girl 2: This is great, Norman!
Phil: Is this goodbye?
Boy 3: But why so sudden?
Boy 4: We’re gonna miss him,
aren’t we?
( Boy 3 stammers ) Uh-huh.
- Girl 3: Congwats!
- ( Norman laughs )
Girl 2: Let’s play a bunch
before you go.
( Overlapping chatter )
( Norman chuckles )
Girl 4: I’m gonna miss you.
girl 5:
I’m gonna miss you.
- ( Girl 1 sniffling )
- ( Norman gasps )
Girl 1: I’m happy for you.
Girl 6: Don’t cry.
Girl 1: Congratulations, Norman.
( Crying )
( Norman chuckles )
I’m gonna miss you all so much.
( Chatter and crying continue )
( Ray grunts )
( Isabella gasps )
( Don shudders )
( Gilda whimpers )
Isabella: Now let’s eat dinner
before it gets cold.
( Boy laughing )
( Boy 2 yelps )
( Laughing )
- ( Boy 3 gasps )
- Don: Found you!
( Both laugh )
Don: Gonna get you!
( Phil laughs )
( Isabella sighs )
( Both laugh )
Boy 4: I feel really clean now.
Girl: Mom!
♪
( Light bulb crackling )
( Clock ticking )
( Norman gasps )
What’s this?
♪
( Woman vocalizing )
( Norman panting )
( Overlapping chatter )
- Ray: Don’t worry.
- ( Emma gasps )
Ray: It’ll work out.
Emma: Norman.
( Norman panting )
( Grunts )
( Electricity crackles )
( Grunting )
( Sighs )
( Grunts )
( Yells )
( Grunting )
( Music ends )
( Wind blowing )
( Sighs )
( Chuckles )
( Birds chirping )
( Children chattering,
laughing )
( Isabella gasps )
Where’s Norman?
( Ray gasps )
( Isabella sighs )
( Ray and Emma chuckle )
♪
( Ray chuckles )
( Emma chuckles )
( Don shudders )
( Gilda gasps )
( Isabella sighs )
( Both gasp )
Isabella: Oh, good.
You’re back...
Norman.
( Emma gasps )
( Ray shudders )
( Groans )
( Footsteps crunching )
( Chatter continues )
Girl: I wanna have
all the red leaves.
Girl 2: Hey, can we go inside?!
- Child: Yeah!
- Child 2: Yeah!
Emma: But why?
( Both gasp )
( Norman chuckles )
ray: Idiot!
What are you thinking?!
Emma: There’s still time
for you to get away!
- Norman: Sorry.
- ( Both gasp )
Norman: I don’t intend to run,
but please just hear me out.
- ( Emma gasps )
- ( Ray grunts )
( Gasps )
( Clock ticking )
Norman: It was a cliff.
- Emma: Huh?
- ( Ray gasps )
Norman: Beyond the wall is...
A cliff.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )