( Singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
( Clock ticking )
( Krone grunts )
( Gasps )
"Number 18684, sister krone...
we appoint you
to be mom of plant four."
( Gasps ) I’ll be a mom?!
Isabella: Yes.
( Krone sighs )
Isabella: It just so happens
a position suddenly opened
at plant four.
I’ve been pushing your name
for a while,
so they chose you to fill it.
Krone: You recommended me?
isabella: Grandma is
waiting for you at the gate.
Hurry up, and pack so you
can return to headquarters.
Krone: Wait. Right now?
Isabella: That’s correct.
I wish you luck
at your new location.
( Krone panting )
( Clock ticking )
Isabella: What’s wrong?
Aren’t you happy?
Krone: Oh, of course I am.
I’ll go get ready.
( Isabella chuckles )
( Footsteps recede )
( Krone gasps )
( Panting )
that woman,
she trying to get rid of me.
I’m just gonna have to risk it.
I refuse to let all of this
go the way that she wants!
( Bell ringing )
Phil: Hey, mom, sister krone!
It’s time to eat now!
( Isabella chuckles )
Phil: Okay, we’re ready.
Where’s the sister?
Girl: In her room?
Isabella: Not quite.
She had work to do.
we’re fine
to start eating without her.
( Krone sighs )
( Thunder rumbling )
( Chains clanking )
Grandma.
( Grandma chuckles )
( Krone swallows )
I’d like to report something.
( Grunts )
( Children chattering )
Girl: Huh? Sister’s not here.
Boy: Where do you think she is?
Phil: Mom said she had to work.
Boy and girl: Aw, man!
Child: That was hard.
( Krone sighs )
grandma: If i’m
understanding this correctly,
in addition to what
i’m reading right here,
there are two other children
with perfect scores
who know the secret.
Krone: And the two
below them know as well!
I don’t have evidence
of their escape plan,
but please believe me!
We have to take action!
- If we don’t, then--
- grandma: But...
They’re still under control,
aren’t they?
Krone: Huh?
grandma: If they remain
under control, there’s no issue.
Just like it was back in my day.
( Krone shudders )
Grandma: You see, sister krone,
i’m afraid I can’t have you
getting in isabella’s way.
In case you don’t know,
Isabella and her plant
are quite special.
it’s necessary
to keep her here as my pawn.
You are insufficient
to replace her.
You’ve become a problem.
( Krone gasps )
grandma: To offer
the best plate at the tifari,
everything at the farm
has to be optimal.
( Krone sighs )
( Laughs )
I see. They were in it together.
( Laughing )
I had no chance...
Of winning this from the start.
( Laughing )
( Thudding footsteps )
( Krone gasps )
( Demon screeches )
isabella:
Thank you for the food.
children:
Thank you for the food!
( Gate squeals )
♪
( Overlapping chatter )
( Isabella chuckles )
( Krone gasping )
( Demon growling )
( Krone chuckling )
♪
( Music playing only )
( Gasping )
( Demon screeches )
( Krone panting )
♪
( Panting )
( Whimpering )
( Demon growling )
♪
( Music playing only )
( Panting )
( Grunts )
( Crackling )
- ( Demon hisses )
- ( Krone gasps )
♪
( Shuddering )
- ( Stab )
- ( Krone screams )
Krone: You brats better
succeed. You hear me?
Krone:You’re great
at tag, so...
Krone: Run away.
Escape.
Krone: Survive this...
Krone: And then destroy
this awful world we live in!
♪
Children: Thank you!
It was delicious!
( Clock ticking )
( Knock on door )
Ray: Are you ready?
Time to switch stuff out.
( Isabella chuckles )
Ray: Let’s review.
norman and Emma
will inspect above the wall.
don and gilda,
stand outside where you can see
the second-floor window
to the south.
Stay alert. I’ll signal to you
if i’m not able to distract mom,
and that’s when
you two tell the others
to cancel the inspection.
Gilda: I hope
this goes smoothly.
Isabella: I got rid of her.
( Ray gasps )
Huh?
Isabella: I removed krone
from the equation.
( Ray gasps )
( Isabella chuckles )
( Ray gasping )
( Clock ticking )
( Footsteps approaching )
Isabella: Know why she’s gone?
Because I didn’t need her.
( Ray gasps )
Isabella: And you’re next.
Ray: Huh?
isabella: Our deal is
officially over as of right now.
Ray: What? Y-you’re joking!
Come on! How can you say
you don’t need me?!
I was helpful to you, right?
You were using me
so you could stay in the shadows
and control them indirectly!
Isabella: Precisely.
Ray: I was doing a good job.
To you, i’m...
Isabella: Yes, you were
quite the useful dog.
That’s why I kept you
by my side.
despite the fact
you’re a liar and a traitor.
( Ray gasps )
( Isabella chuckles )
i can still be
of use to you, though!
It’s a non-issue!
( Coughs )
( Grunts )
Isabella: Yes.
it’s true
there’s no fault with you.
I know that it’s unfair.
It affects me as well.
Initially, I had planned
to keep you around
until the very end of all this.
- ray: That doesn’t--
- Isabella: But unfortunately
the situation has changed.
I’ll be controlling them
on my own from now on.
( Ray gasps )
Isabella: I’m sorry, ray.
I hope you’ll forgive me
for what i’m about to do.
( Ray gasps )
( Grunts )
( Isabella chuckles )
( Ray grunts )
( Door creaks )
Mom!
Isabella: Just stay
in there for a while.
( Ray gasping )
Isabella: I’ll be sure
to let you out when i’m back.
( Pounding on door )
now, then, based on
the speed of the two signals,
it must be Emma and Norman.
So they’re running
through the forest,
heading for the fence,
I assume, to inspect it.
- ( Ray gasps )
- Isabella: By the way,
i’m not the least bit worried
about the poison.
I know that you’ll protect me.
for their sake,
you won’t get me killed.
Isn’t that right?
that’s why,
when you try to suppress me,
I know you’ll use
a different method.
( Ray gasps )
Isabella: Goodbye, ray.
Thank you for all
that you’ve done for me.
♪
Ray: Damn it! ( Groans )
No! I’ve gotta get out of here!
( Grunts )
I can’t believe this!
Don: Huh. Nothin’.
Gilda: Yeah.
Don: So far, so good.
- ( Door closes )
- ( Gilda gasps )
( Don gasps )
Gilda: Wait. What’s going on?
Mom came out even though
ray didn’t signal us.
( Footstep echoes )
Gilda: Don, what should we do?
Don: Stay here.
I’ll go check it out.
- gilda: Don!
- Don: I’ll be right back!
( Gilda shudders )
( Pounding )
( Ray grunts )
( Groans )
Just open up, already.
Don: Ray, is that you?
Ray: Yeah, it’s me!
- Don: Stand back!
- ray: Eh?
( Running footsteps )
- ( Don moans )
- Ray: Hey, you okay?
Don: I’m fine.
But we gotta hurry!
Ray: Yeah. You’re right!
( Gilda sighing )
Don: Gilda, let’s go!
Gilda: Does that mean
the plan’s cancelled?
What do we do now?
Don: The inspection is still on!
We gotta stop mom!
Gilda: Huh? Really?
Don: This is our only chance!
We need to make sure they get
to inspect the top of the wall
before mom gets to them!
Gilda: R-right!
( Ray panting )
♪
( Both grunt )
( Emma gasps )
Norman: Emma.
Emma: Yeah.
( Wind blowing )
( Footsteps crunching )
( Emma gasps )
Why is...
Hey, mom.
Is something wrong?
Isabella: Ten years.
Emma: Huh?
Isabella: That’s how long
we’ve been living together,
but this is the first time we’ve
talked without any of us acting.
( Emma grunts )
( Isabella sighs )
It’s nice to meet you, Emma,
and the same
goes for you, Norman.
( Both gasp )
( Isabella laughs )
come, now.
Why do you look so worried?
it’s only me,
so you’re free to relax.
There isn’t anyone else around.
You don’t have to act
like good little kids
who don’t know anything.
Right now, we’re the caretaker
and the children
meant to be food.
( Both gasp )
Isabella: However, I must admit,
I love every one of the children
i’ve raised. I do, truly,
as if you all
were my own children.
That’s why I came out here
to ask that you just give up.
Emma: You want us to...
Norman: Give up?
( Both gasp )
Isabella: Give up resisting.
i love you all
and don’t want you to suffer,
and I especially don’t want
to be the cause
of your suffering.
This life is happy, isn’t it?
You get to live in a warm house
filled with delicious food
and love.
if you can stay
oblivious to the truth,
then you are able to die
feeling satisfied.
So how does that sound
like anything but paradise?
( Emma gasps )
That’s what you think this is?
are you saying
that this "happy life"
was worth what conny
went through?
Isabella: Death happens
in an instant.
Until the moment she died,
conny experienced a rich life
full of smiles and laughter.
( Emma gasps ) What’s the point
if it’s all just fake?!
I’m going to live freely,
even if I suffer for it!
Then i’ll decide happiness
for myself!
( Shudders )
Norman: Stop.
( Grunts )
Emma: Norman...
isabella:
Escaping is impossible,
and it’s dangerous outside.
You don’t really want
to go out there.
Now, why don’t we all go back
to living happily together,
like none of this happened?
My greatest wish is for the five
of you to live joyous lives
until your time
eventually runs out.
Norman: Five? Not three?
( Both grunt )
( Both gasp )
( Both sigh )
Norman: Fine. You win, mom.
( Isabella chuckles )
Norman: I’ll stop
being a good kid.
Isabella: Huh?
Isabella: Go, Norman!
( Chuckles )
( Crack )
( Norman gasps )
( Emma gasping )
( Wailing )
( All gasp )
Ray: Emma.
( Emma sobbing )
( Isabella chuckles )
Shh. Shh.
You’re going to be okay.
It doesn’t hurt. Don’t cry.
Aw, poor thing.
My adorable Emma.
this is why
I told you to give up.
But i’m glad you hugged me
for the first time in a while.
( Chuckles )
And you realized it
quickly, Norman.
I’m impressed.
Yes, i’ll control all of you
until the very end,
because you’re different
than most of the other children.
You’re special food that only
a special one is able to eat,
the highest quality of children
i’ve ever raised.
( Emma winces )
♪
Norman: So, then...
Isabella: That’s why
I have to protect you all,
no matter the cost.
I was forced to do this,
because it was clear
you weren’t going to give up.
( Emma gasping )
( Wails )
( Children laughing )
Naila: Mom!
Oh, no! What happened to Emma?
Mark: Did she get hurt?
( Chorus vocalizing )
Boy: Look!
( Boy 2 gasps )
( Children gasp )
Phil: Huh?
( Emma gasps )
Isabella: You won’t be able
to move for a while,
which means i’ll have
no worries for tomorrow.
Ray: Tomorrow?
Isabella: Yes. That’s right.
you can stay
and celebrate, Emma.
( Norman gasps )
isabella: There was
a notice from headquarters,
so, congrats, Norman.
The time for you
to be shipped has come.
( All gasp )
( Norman shuddering )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )