( Singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
( Clock ticking )
( Ray chuckles )
Are you serious? Cut it out.
norman: Ray,
you’ve realized, right?
I set a trap for three people.
i told Don
it was behind my bed,
and gilda was told
it was in the second floor
bathroom’s ceiling.
at least,
that’s what I told you,
but I actually told Don
the dining hall,
and I told gilda the library.
( Ray sighs )
Norman: The rope behind my bed
ended up being gone.
So what about
the other two spots?
Should we go over
and check them out?
( Clock ticking )
( Ray sighs )
( Laughing )
( Laughter continues )
Aw, man.
And here I thought
I was doing so well.
♪
Yeah, you’re right.
i’m the one
who’s been spying for mom.
( Norman sighs )
Ray: So what gave it away?
Norman: It was when sister
first came to the house.
I was disgusted with myself.
I suspected you instantly...
My own friend.
it was really
the worst-case scenario.
i wished that I
had been wrong about it,
because you being the traitor
would be
quite problematic for us,
but, for the enemy, picking you
was the obvious choice.
you would be able
to provide input to our plans,
which would be perfect
for keeping control
of the situation.
You were the best one
for the job.
Ray: Can’t get
anything past you.
How embarrassing.
i walked right
into your little trap.
Norman: There’s one more thing.
You see, I have a feeling
this isn’t the first time
you’ve done this.
If one of us suddenly
started giving mom tips,
I doubt she’d be so trusting.
just how long
have you been mom’s spy?
- Ray: For a while now.
- ( Norman gasps )
I can’t remember
when I wasn’t her spy.
Guess you could say that i’m
a sheepdog for a Shepherd.
Norman: You knew
about all of this
and helped mom out anyway?
Ray: Yeah.
( Chorus vocalizing )
norman:
Everything we talked about,
all the planning,
it was nothing
but a series of lies?
How much have you
been telling mom?
Can the trackers
even be broken?
Ray: What are you gonna do
with that info?
Gonna ditch me
based on my answer?
Norman: No, I won’t.
I want you to stay close,
like you always have been.
( Ray sighs )
Norman: Isn’t it great, ray?
You get to hide your mistake.
You tried framing Don
so you could keep
spying on us, correct?
Ray: Just tell me what you want.
Norman: Three things.
One, you will continue
to stay with us
and promise
to guarantee our safety.
Two, I want you to share
all the information you have.
Three, flip to our side...
( Ray gasps )
norman: And become
a spy for our team instead.
Ray: You’re gonna use me
as your trump card?
- Norman: Hmm.
- Ray: Are you an idiot?
If that was your objective,
then you should’ve kept quiet
and used me,
and, when it was time
to execute the plan,
you could have cast me aside.
It would have been easy!
Norman: You’re right
about that, but...
( Chuckles )
( Ray sighs )
Norman: She reminded me
we’re family, so...
( Clock ticking )
( Ray sighs ) Huh.
Norman: That’s what made me
change my mind.
I wanna believe in you, too.
we’re friends
before enemies, right?
After all...
Aren’t you the one
who hid little bunny?
The night we went to the gate,
if you hadn’t told us
we could make it in time,
we wouldn’t have gone.
You laid out the bread crumbs
for us to find out the truth
about this house for ourselves.
You set this up for the three
of us to escape, didn’t you?
why did you
become mom’s sheepdog?
Ray: Why not?
Norman: If you were
completely on mom’s side,
then it wouldn’t make sense
to reveal the truth to us.
You’ve been controlling
our actions,
about the trackers,
the timing of our escape,
and how quickly
the plan moved forward.
That’s why you didn’t want us
leaving ten days from now.
But, at the same time, you were
also keeping mom under control.
you’re actually
not our enemy, are you?
( Ray chuckles )
You still think that, huh?
- I volunteered.
- ( Norman gasps )
Ray: I guess it’s more like
I sold myself, really.
And all of it was to prepare
for the escape
we’re planning!
( Norman gasps )
Ray: If you’re going to learn
more about the enemy,
it’s best to do so
from the inside,
which is why I ended up
offering a deal to mom.
Norman: That’s risky.
Ray: Not really.
I’m one of the finest products
she’s raised here.
She cared a lot for me.
She wouldn’t throw me away.
That’s how I saw it.
She’s someone who cares more
about profit than rules.
i made sure
to ask for two things.
First was not to be shipped out
if I cooperated.
The second was rewards
in exchange for results.
Norman: What kind of rewards?
Ray: Various junk.
If it isn’t in the house,
she secures it for me.
- Norman: Huh?
- ( Ray grunts )
My reason for doing it
was to check what I
could and couldn’t get,
but also to research
the outside.
turns out,
as long as it was safe,
she could get me lots of things,
but everything
she brings back is dated.
norman: So, then,
when you said you had an idea
for breaking the trackers...
Ray: I’ve seen the real device.
I did testing.
It took me a few years,
but I figured it out.
it is possible
to break the tracking devices.
- ( Norman gasps )
- Ray: You get it?
Norman, i’m the strongest card
you’ll ever have.
No one else compares.
And I don’t just have info about
the tracking devices and mom.
You can’t even begin to imagine
how much i’ve learned
over the years.
from the moment
that I discovered the truth,
I started preparing.
Norman: Ray...
Ray: I had you and Emma
go to the gate
without having anyone notice.
All of this, just to make sure
you both don’t die!
( Norman gasps )
Ray: It’s like you said, Norman.
I’m not exactly your enemy,
but i’m not your ally either.
Let’s make a deal.
if you agree,
i’ll become your trump card.
I’ll tell you everything I know
and leak false info to mom
if you do one thing.
Norman: What’s that?
- Ray: Trick Emma.
- ( Norman gasps )
Ray: We’ll pretend
we’re taking everyone,
then ditch them later,
but we can take Don
and gilda, too.
Norman: Are you saying we should
give up escaping with everyone?
- ray: Yes.
- Norman: But the training
helped them grow
more than we expected.
you even said
that they had potential.
You meant it, didn’t you?
- Then, all of us can--
- ray: Regardless,
it doesn’t change the fact
that they’re a huge burden.
( Sighs )
Norman: You said you were going
to help us, didn’t you, ray?
Ray: What i’m doing now
is helping.
You don’t like it,
then you two can die here.
Norman: But I thought you wanted
me and Emma to stay alive.
ray: Honestly,
i’d rather you get shipped
than die once we escape.
( Norman sighs )
Ray: So do we have a deal?
Fine, then.
( Gasps )
ray: Listen,
if I find out you lied to me...
Norman: Don’t worry.
I’ll keep my word.
♪
( Gasping )
( Ray chuckles )
( Norman sighs )
( Gasps )
( Chuckles )
( Gasping )
( Ray groans )
( Door creaks )
( Clock ticking )
Isabella: What took so long?
Ray: Just talking to Norman.
Isabella: About what?
Not much has changed.
They’re still training
by playing tag.
The problem is sister.
She’s on the move yet again,
so be careful.
Isabella: Oh.
Ray: It wasn’t a smart move
to summon her here.
I mean, I know you only did it
to deter me.
I’ve helped you for six years,
and you still
don’t fully trust me.
I might cry.
isabella:
It’s merely a precaution,
but I hope you’re aware
that had you kept those two
away from the gate,
then we wouldn’t even be
in this situation.
Ray: I said sorry.
Isabella: I never thought
that someone like you
was capable of failing
such a simple task.
I wasn’t really
asking for much.
Ray: I already made up for that
by spying for you.
I ratted on my friends,
and I report
every move sister krone makes,
so you better
give me my reward.
Isabella: Well, of course.
That is part of our deal.
( Children panting )
Norman: We’re all going
to escape this place together!
That means ray, too!
( Gasping )
Ray: See? And this is why...
I tried to tell you.
Norman: Emma!
( Gasps )
Emma.
Everyone.
( Demon hissing )
( Norman screams )
Boy: Time to get up, nor-man!
( Norman panting )
( Boy giggles )
( Girl giggles )
Norman: Uh...
Good morning.
( Both laughing )
( Overlapping chatter )
( Boy giggles )
Emma: Morning, Norman!
Norman: Oh, hey. Morning!
Ray: Morning, Norman.
- Norman: Morning, ray.
- Mark: Hi, Emma!
emma: So?
What happened with the rope?
Did you find out
who the informant is?
Norman: Actually...
Ray: Oh. That?
- it’s me.
- ( Norman gasps )
ray: I’m the one
who’s been leaking info.
Emma: Uh...
It was you?!
Uh...
( Sighs )
oh, uh,
sorry ’bout that reaction,
but I don’t really understand,
- so can you please...
- Norman: Uh, right!
- Emma: Help me?
- Norman: Let me explain!
Emma: So, ray is mom’s spy,
but he’s not our enemy,
and the reason why he was
helping mom this entire time
was for our sake?
Norman: Yeah.
ray: The truth is
I was planning on telling you,
as soon as you came back
from the gate, in fact.
( Sighs ) But you left
little bunny behind
and mentioned
bringing everyone with,
so I had no choice
but to hold off.
Then mom found out,
which meant
I had to work around all that
while also handling
your reckless actions.
I figured it was best
to stay quiet
and keep things under control.
Emma: Basically
you were covering up
the mistake
that Norman and I made.
are you still
against escaping with everyone?
’cause we could use your help.
Ray: I had a change of heart,
so I will help you escape
with everyone.
( Emma gasps )
That’s unlike you.
( Ray gasps )
Norman: Do you think he’s lying?
Emma: Mm-mmm. I’m glad!
Having ray there
to help everyone escape
is gonna be great!
and now we have
all kinds of info to use
so we can trick mom
from the inside!
We’re at an advantage!
Although, that means...
You knew for a long time,
didn’t you?
( Norman sighs )
Emma: I bet it was tough,
knowing and
sending them all off,
so many of our siblings.
♪
Hey, about the tracking devices,
they were tested
on our siblings, weren’t they?
( Ray and Norman gasp )
Emma: So, then, tell me.
What happened to all those kids?
you didn’t make them
get shipped out early, did you?
I sincerely hope you didn’t
sacrifice someone for us.
( Ray sighs )
Emma: Actually,
I should thank you.
Because of that,
all of us can run away.
But...
you have to promise me
that you’ll never do that again.
( Scraping )
You’re not alone.
You’ve got us now, so...
( Ray sighs )
All right, fine.
I give you my word.
Let’s all escape
from here together.
Gilda: The three of them
are talking privately
in the forest again.
( Don growls )
How long are we
just gonna stand around
and plan?!
We gotta save conny
as soon as possible.
gilda: What if
something’s preventing us?
Don: What do you mean?
Gilda: I don’t really know.
- Phil: Ready, set, go!
- Gilda: Something tells me
this isn’t dangerous
just because of bad people.
It’s more than that, much more.
Ray: She was pretty mad,
i guess.
norman: By the way,
I wanted to ask you something.
Ray: Yeah? What’s up?
Norman: You said before
that you did this
so Emma and I wouldn’t die.
You’re not planning to...
Emma: Oh, yeah!
There was something
I had to report.
Boys: Hmm?
Emma: Gilda and I decided
to observe mom again,
and we noticed
something strange.
she disappears
right before 8:00 every night.
Norman: She does?
Emma: Yeah. There are
no traces of her anywhere...
Meaning there’s a secret room
in this house.
Don: Whoa. Really?
Emma: Yeah, located here.
It’s right next
to mom’s bedroom.
Mom’s room is connected to both
the bathroom and washroom,
and then, past that,
behind the wall,
is where her office is,
but from what i’ve gathered,
this probably isn’t a wall.
Gilda: Mm. As for me,
what I noticed
was that she disappears
into either the office
or the washroom.
Emma: That said,
I measured the distance
of the inside of the room,
along with the hallway
outside of it.
norman: Oh!
That’s what you were doing.
- Don: Huh?
- Emma: Yeah.
Don: Okay. And?
Emma: They didn’t match.
There’s about ten steps
worth of space here.
one side’s a wall,
the other has bookshelves,
but i’m guessing there are
hidden doors on both sides.
Gilda: And beyond those doors
is mom’s secret room.
don: Why does
something like that even exist?
Emma: It’s probably for--
ray: Standard check-ins.
I bet that’s where she goes
to check in
with the headquarters every day.
- Makes the most sense.
- ( Girls gasp )
Don: Headquarters?
Norman: The base
that supplies babies
and sisters like krone
to this house.
( Don gasps )
Emma: I’m curious, ray.
Did you know about the room?
ray: No, but I
had a feeling it existed.
Don: Let’s try to get in!
’cause what if
there’s a way to, like,
talk to the outside in there?
or some clues
about conny and the others?
Gilda: But don’t you think
it’ll be hard to get in?
Don: Who cares?
We still have to try!
Ray: Hold it.
There’s no advantage
in doing that.
I’ve got a strong feeling
that the transmission device
only connects with hq.
As for where our siblings were
sent to, mom wouldn’t know,
so I don’t think
we’d find any clues.
And don’t forget the trackers
could show her we’re snooping.
That is if the security
in the room doesn’t first.
- It’s too risky.
- Don: Yeah, but--
ray: I’m trying to tell you
that the risks
greatly outweigh the benefits.
( Don gasps )
Norman: I agree,
and we still
have to worry about krone,
so it’s not really wise
to make foolish moves.
Ray: Exactly.
I’ve still got mom
under control,
but we’re done for
if krone finds out.
Keep that in mind.
( Don sighs )
( Gilda sighs )
Ray: Don, do me a favor,
and go make dinner, please.
If one of us doesn’t go, then--
Don: Yeah, I know!
Gilda: Huh?
Don, but that’s...
( Don sighs )
Gilda: Are you really going in?
Don: I can’t just stay calm
like the rest of them.
( Gilda sighs )
Don: And I wanna know mom.
I mean the real mom.
( Gilda grunts )
( Both grunt )
( Clock ticking )
Don: There’s a hidden door
behind this thing.
( Grunting )
( Gilda gasps )
Don: Why won’t it budge?
( Grunting )
( Wood creaking, groaning )
- ( Growls )
- ( Gilda gasps )
Don: Is it really even here?!
Damn! We have to hurry up
and find some clues
that’ll help us rescue conny!
Gilda: Maybe...
( Don gasps ) Huh?
Gilda: Take a closer look
at the shape.
Don: Ah.
Hmm.
Come on.
Oh, man. It’s locked.
- ( Doorknob turns )
- ( Both gasp )
( Door creaking )
( Both gasp )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )