( Singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
Isabella: I’ve set aside
this room for you.
Krone: Thank you. It’s perfect.
Ray: That’s sure
gonna be inconvenient.
emma: She’s between
the three childrens’s rooms.
Norman: It’ll be easier
for her to watch us.
( Children laugh )
( Overlapping chatter )
( Child grunts )
Norman: I was so focused
on the trackers
that another adult
never crossed my mind.
Ray: We should
be happy about this.
Emma: Huh? What do you mean?
Ray: With Carol
and sister krone here,
we have
two new sources of info.
Norman: You’re right.
ray: First off,
where did they both come from?
Norman: I suppose carol’s here
to replace conny.
they must
replenishing merchandise.
ray: Yeah,
if this place is a farm,
they must have a base where they
prepare all the one-year-olds
to resupply the house.
emma: So then,
do you think we all came
from that place at some point?
Ray: Probably. And I bet
sister krone did, too.
Norman: It’s significant that
there are adults other than mom.
it means there might be
other farms similar to this one.
Are the adults who work for
the demons under their control
from the time they’re born
or after they’re captured?
knowing could change
how we survive after escaping.
Ray: But, first,
we need to find out
how to escape with everyone,
plus find
the tracking devices.
Emma: I’ve searched
all over my body,
but there are no scars
to show something was implanted.
norman:
Nothing in our clothes either.
Ray: Just based on mankind’s
existing technology,
they probably use radio waves
and need batteries.
Something battery powered,
that’s small,
doesn’t leave a scar,
and lasts over 10 years,
that kind of technology
wouldn’t exist in 2015.
Emma: Meaning?
Ray: It’s going to be difficult
to find the location and
then figure out how to break it.
And if it’s demon technology,
we may as well give up.
Norman: You’re right.
Emma: Huh? That’s it?
Ray: Pretty much.
Emma: That’s awful!
Norman: Well...
If we can’t solve it,
we can guess.
ray: Right.
Let’s think like them.
It might help.
what would be the most
convenient place to put it in?
Emma: Mm...
( Clock ticking )
- ( Norman gasps ) Carol.
- Emma: Huh?
Ray: She might still have
a Mark, since she just arrived.
( Emma gasps )
From where they put the device.
( Phil panting )
krone: I’d like
to thank you personally
for giving me the opportunity
to come back to this side.
isabella:
I simply made a request
to have an assistant provided.
it’s not like
I called for you specifically.
Krone: I’ve heard a number
of good things about you,
like how you’re the youngest
ever to be selected
as a mom and caretaker
and producing
the highest-grade merchandise
among any
of the plantations ever.
For me to get to work
under someone I admire,
I am truly honored.
isabella: I have
no need for lip service,
and I have no time
for small talk.
Now, then, let’s get to work.
these files cover
each of my precious children.
Memorize all of them right now.
It should be easier
than getting perfect scores
on your daily test.
( Krone chuckles )
Out of curiosity,
why did you decide
to call for an assistant?
isabella:
They discovered the secret.
( Krone gasps )
Isabella: And they
saw the truck as well.
krone: Well,
according to the rules,
we must find them
and ship them out now!
isabella:
Now hold it right there.
It’s all right.
I already have a good idea
of who the targets are.
Krone: You do?
isabella: Likely,
two of the older children.
We just have to ensure they
don’t escape before shipment.
"special" doesn’t even
begin to describe my children,
and this is all beneficial
for the plant.
Krone: So you’re
not reporting it?
isabella: Not yet.
I have procedures in place
to deal with this,
and you are my guard.
don’t think.
Just watch the children.
I am the mom of this house,
and you are nothing more
than an assistant.
Do you understand, sister krone?
Krone: Of course, miss Isabella.
( Chuckles )
So that’s how it is!
It’s so surprising.
To think that
the amazing Isabella
would make such a huge mistake.
and she’s
not reporting any of it,
instead trying
to cover up her failure.
if I help her,
she’ll owe me big time,
and i’ll be rewarded
for my hard work
with a mom position
to call my own!
Oh, my. What’s wrong, sweetie?
Why are you crying so much,
my precious one?
Come on now. Don’t cry.
You’d be happy,
too, wouldn’t you,
if I was promoted to a mom?
If that happens,
i’ll be much busier,
but you’ll always be here to
support me, won’t you, my dear?
Just try not to get jealous
and act selfishly
because i’m paying attention
to the other children.
Wait a minute.
You really think so?
this could be
my chance to move up?
then I can
finally become a mom!
And I won’t have to wait,
because my time is now!
If I were able to capture
the children
who know the secret
and report her violation
to the higher-ups,
then Isabella will be fired!
I think it’s best
to pretend to obey her,
and then,
when she least expects it,
- take her position away!
- ( Thumps )
♪ I’ll capture the targets
♪ snitch on her
♪ then immediately ship
the kids out for processing ♪
( Squeals )
That’s it!
I’m going to be
the mom of this house.
I need to find those brats fast.
( Insects chirping )
( Overlapping chatter )
Norman: The kids all adore her.
- Girl: Hey, me next!
- ray: Yeah.
how do we make
someone out to be the bad guy
when everyone loves them?
- Norman: Exactly.
- ( Dishes clatter )
i’m more worried
about the demons being notified.
As soon as they know
we’ve escaped,
they’re gonna come after us.
Ray: There’s only one way
we can prevent that.
The grown-ups will have to be...
- ( Child laughs )
- Child 2: Don’t move.
( Chatter quiets )
( Norman gasps )
Krone: You’re Norman,
and you’re ray, correct?
Ray: Yeah.
krone: I heard
you get perfect test scores.
- Norman: Yes.
- Krone: That’s amazing.
Nice to meet you.
I know we’ll get along.
( Chuckles )
Norman: Uh...
( Krone chuckles )
Ray: Did she hear us?
Norman: No. We’re okay.
That woman...
I don’t think she came here
simply to watch children.
Ray: What are you saying?
Norman: The way
she looked at us,
she suspects us,
since we’re the oldest.
ray: Wait a sec.
How’d she find that out?
Norman: Isn’t it obvious?
mom told her.
- ( Ray grunts )
- Norman: Mom is on our trail,
and she’s closing in on us.
- ( Carol cooing )
- Norman: Let’s hurry.
( Clock ticking )
( Carol laughing )
( Girl grunts )
( Carol giggles )
Emma: Shift perspective.
Try to think like them.
Demons won’t eat
the tracking device,
which means...
It’s somewhere easy to remove.
Girl: Emma, I, uh...
Emma: But where?
girl: Wanted
to ask you something.
The other night...
( Carol coos )
Girl: What’s that?
Is it a bug bite?
Emma: No, it’s--it’s a Mark
from when they
took our blood for testing.
At least, that’s what mom said.
- ( Carol coos )
- ( Emma gasps )
Naila had it when she came!
So did Mark, Phil, and conny!
On everybody’s ear.
Girl: Mine, too?
Emma: No, it’s already gone.
Girl: That makes sense,
though, right?
I’m 10, and you’re 11,
so it’s been years now.
Emma: Yeah. It was way smaller
than I expected it to be.
Girl: What was?
Emma: Huh?
Oh! I was talking
about the scar
and how tiny it was.
It disappeared already!
Girl: Yeah.
( Carol fussing )
( Cooing )
I’ve gotta protect them,
every last one.
Isabella: Regular check-in.
Regular check-in.
This is 73584 at plant three.
October 17th, situation normal.
Ending transmission.
Woman: Isabella?
Isabella: Grandma?
Grandma: I have a message
for you from the boss.
"those three
can still be shipped out
as scheduled, correct?"
( Isabella sighs )
Grandma: Listen, Isabella.
The other plants
had a disappointing harvest
this year,
and only your plant can deliver
the highest quality goods
that are going to be offered
during tifari.
Isabella: Yes, I understood that
from the start.
Please tell the boss,
"everything is going fine.
You may have any child
whenever you wish."
demon: I see.
So they can be shipped?
The one will most certainly
be pleased by this news.
don’t fail us.
Only the most special meal
can be presented to the one,
unlike our fare.
Now let us celebrate
the coming harvest
and offer prayers to the one.
Atter )
( Girl sighs )
( Emma grunts )
Aww!
( Child giggles )
Ray: Yeah, they’re in a place
no one would notice.
Norman: I never knew
about a Mark
from when they took our blood,
and it disappears that quickly?
Emma: Yeah. I knew,
but I never even considered
that would be it.
Sorry.
Norman: Oh, no.
You did great, Emma.
We now know the location
and the size of the device.
On to the next step.
Emma: The next step is...
All: How to break it.
Norman: Let’s see.
If we tried to make
an incision...
Emma: Mom might lift our hair
and see it.
Norman: She’d catch on.
Ray: You’re right.
well, whether or not
we can break the transmitters,
the tracking devices
implanted in us
aren’t that useful
in the grand scheme of things.
emma: What?
How do you figure that?
Ray: The signal’s so crude,
it can’t specify an individual.
without checking,
she can’t tell where we are.
Even if we get close
to the gate or walls,
it doesn’t notify her.
Emma: But we still have them.
Ray: Yes, but why?
They must be confident
they can come after us
as long as
the tracking device is intact.
Norman: Hold on.
so that means if it
were to send a notification,
it’d only be
after it’s been destroyed?
ray: That’s
a definite possibility.
Emma: What do you guys mean?
Ray: Weren’t you listening?
An alarm probably goes off
once the trackers are broken.
emma: So mom
would find out instantly?
Ray: If a notification function
really exists.
Norman: But knowing
that mom purposefully
clued us in
on the existence of the devices,
we can’t ignore the risk.
Ray: It’s dangerous
to even touch it.
Norman: So we can only
destroy it when we escape.
emma: What?
But how do we deal with it?
We have to know!
Ray: Actually,
i’ve been thinking.
The shape and size of it
brings something else to mind.
leave it to me.
I’ll figure out a work-around.
Norman: You sure?
Ray: Uh-huh.
Emma: If you say so.
It’s all yours.
Norman: Now the issue of taking
the other children with us.
the problem is
they all completely trust mom,
and they probably
won’t be able to handle
the truth of our situation.
Emma: If we want
to take them, too,
we’re gonna have to lie to them?
Ray: There’s another issue,
insufficient abilities.
To put it bluntly,
they’re a hindrance.
Emma: Ray!
Ray: You know it’s the truth.
Some of them aren’t good
at physical activity,
not to mention the babies
who can hardly walk.
Emma: I actually have an idea
for how to deal with that.
Norman: Which is?
Emma: By playing tag.
Boys: Huh?
Emma: Norman is it,
and everybody else runs.
Norman: We pretend it’s play
when we’re actually training.
Norman: Then mom won’t find out!
Emma: I’ll teach them how to
push their bodies to the limit.
As for sharpening their minds...
Boys: Leave it to us.
( Children yell )
Ray: Don’t rush.
- boy: Eh?
- Ray: Concentrate.
- What can you do to escape?
- Boy: Hmm.
Ray: Norman isn’t going
to overlook any details.
Boy: Huh.
♪
( Grunting )
Ray: Check the wind.
Which way is easier to run?
Don: Let’s see now.
That’s downwind.
Emma: Shh!
( Children stammering )
Boy 2: This is awesome.
I can last way longer
than I did before!
Maybe I can even beat Norman.
( Shrieks )
And I thought I was doing
so good this time, too!
Ray: You can’t just focus
on your own footprints.
You gotta check out
norman’s too.
- Boy 2: Really?
- Ray: That’s right.
You also have to realize that
Norman is reading your habits.
As an example--hmm?
( Children laughing )
Krone: Outside playing tag.
Looks like fun.
It’s important that I get
to know all of you better,
so let me join in.
This match will have
a 20-minute time limit.
I’ll be it this round.
Now then, run and hide!
( Boy 3 laughs )
Krone: 7, 8, 9, and 10.
Now I get to see for myself
exactly what isabella’s crop
of special children can do!
Let the game begin!
ray: Now, then,
how will the enemy move?
Norman: She’ll probably
come looking for us first.
Ray: And on the way,
she’ll take out
the younger, slower ones.
Makes the most sense.
Krone: Fake footprints?
That’s strange.
How is it so quiet?
I’m gonna have to play
for real, then!
♪
( Children murmuring )
Emma: She’s not coming after us.
Ray: What’s she planning?
- Girl: What’s this?
- boy: Huh?
- ( Krone panting )
- ( Emma gasps )
Krone: Guess I got you!
Emma: How’d she
draw them all in?!
Norman: She left these
on the ground to lure them.
ray: So she’s got
a good head on her shoulders.
( Don gasps )
( Girls giggle )
( Clock ticking )
( Boy 1 wails )
( Sighs )
( Krone giggles )
( Boy 1 whimpers )
I can’t believe it!
She’s impossible to beat!
Huh?
Don and gilda, too?
Don: She’s crazy fast.
I couldn’t get away.
gilda: You’re right.
She caught us in way less time
than it usually takes Norman.
Phil: Hey, Emma!
Emma: Cover your mouths.
( Krone panting )
( Laughs )
Eh?
Running while carrying two kids
takes stamina.
You must be exhausted, Emma.
( Emma breathing heavily )
Krone: You won’t be able
to move unless you rest.
Know what i’ve learned?
Norman’s failing point
is his physical strength.
I heard he was feeble
when he was younger.
Ray’s weakness
is that he’s always
a little too quick to give up.
He tends to make fast decisions,
but then abandons them
just as quickly.
And you, Emma,
your weakness is your naiveté,
like carrying others
when you’re being chased,
since they’d be
helpless otherwise.
Give up, and come out, already!
I swear I won’t do you wrong.
Listen, Emma, why don’t we
level with each other?
If you saw the harvest
the other day,
then you should know
i’m on your side.
I found you.
( Children stammer )
Boy 1: Two more to go!
Don: How much time
does she have?
Boy 4: Eight minutes,
40 seconds!
♪
Krone: They are truly elite.
( Clock ticking )
( Krone gasps )
Ray: Your time’s up.
( Krone sighs )
( Children cheering )
Krone: Norman, ray, Emma.
( Emma laughs )
Krone: And...
( Chuckles )
Emma: Krone hasn’t
done anything since then.
It seems strange.
Norman: She’s probably
just following mom’s orders.
Mom used to suspect us at first,
but it doesn’t
seem like that now.
Emma: I wonder what happened?
Norman: Thoughts, ray?
ray: I’d like to hear
what you’re thinking, Norman.
norman: I think mom
did something behind the scenes
so that she wouldn’t
have to make a move herself.
- Emma: What do you mean?
- Norman: Think like mom.
What’s the easiest situation
you could hope for?
Emma: Uh...
norman: Knowing
your target’s every move
without ever
having to do anything yourself.
emma: But you said
there are no hidden cameras
or listening devices.
( Gasping )
It couldn’t be.
Norman: That’s right. I think--
ray: There’s another person
keeping an eye on us,
and it’s someone among the kids.
Norman: So there’s a traitor.
( Emma gasps )
- ( Bell ringing )
- ( Phil chuckling )
( Overlapping chatter )
( Phil laughs )
( Distorted chatter echoing )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )