Krone: Hmm?
Gilda: Join forces?
Norman: It’s fine, you guys.
- No need to worry.
- ( All gasp )
Norman: We’ll hear you out.
( Krone chuckles )
excellent.
It’s best if we cooperate
so we can each
achieve our goals.
you all want
to break out of here,
and I want to eventually
become mom of this house.
The plan is to drag Isabella
from her position
and then seize it for myself.
Don: You wanna be a mom?
Krone: To prove that I mean it,
you kids aren’t the only ones
who wanna break free from this.
( All gasp )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
krone: Are you aware
of the management system here?
( All gasp )
Krone: Girls who meet
certain conditions
and live until the age of 12
are usually presented
with two different paths when
they’re about to be shipped out,
continue and die
or aim to become a mom.
Don: What conditions?
Krone: High test scores
and the mom’s recommendation.
Meet those two requirements,
and it’s possible to survive
without escaping,
if you’re a girl.
Gilda: Only girls?
Krone: Although,
I don’t recommend it.
They make it so you’re never
allowed to leave the premises.
( All gasp )
Emma: What is that?
Krone: There’s a chip inside,
and, with it, if you step
one foot outside the farm,
an electric current triggers
and causes your heart to stop.
( All gasp )
Krone: But, at the same time,
if your heart stops
for some other reason,
it acts as a transmitter
that notifies the higher-ups.
Norman: We were right about
not being able to kill them.
( Krone chuckles )
because of this chip,
I can only live on the farms.
That’s why I wanna live
in the best way
this place has to offer.
- ( Emma sighs )
- Krone: Even if it’s fake,
being a mom means
you get to feel human,
but, to achieve that,
I have to remove Isabella.
If all of you escape, she’ll be
the one who’s blamed for it.
( Giggles ) Trust me,
i won’t stop you
if you make a run for it.
It actually benefits me.
Gilda: You won’t ship us out?
- Krone: Of course not.
- ( Gilda and Don gasp )
Krone: So let’s cooperate!
( Don groans )
( Emma grunts )
( Norman sighs )
( Krone chuckles )
How about it?
Emma: Norman.
Wait a sec.
I wanna make sure of something.
Krone: What is it?
Krone: How can we be sure
you’re not gonna
betray us in the end?
Krone: Are you saying
you don’t trust me?
Emma: Answer!
( Krone scoffs )
All right.
if ray goes
and tattles on me to mom,
you can destroy me.
Meanwhile, if I tell mom that
ray’s acting as a double agent,
then all of you
will go down with him.
so, you see,
neither of us will snitch,
because we can’t.
Do you trust me now?
( Emma sighs )
Yeah, sure.
Krone: I guess
we have a deal, then.
♪
( Chuckles )
I know a lot of info
about this place
that may be helpful
for you to know,
and i’m willing
to share it with you all.
It’s proof of my goodwill.
If you’re interested,
why don’t you
drop by my room tonight?
( Children chattering,
laughing )
Emma: She was one of us,
and yet this is just
so she can have a better life.
What a monster.
She doesn’t care
if any of the kids here
live or die at all.
gilda: She said
she won’t ship us, though.
Norman: What she meant
was she can’t.
If she really
wanted us to escape,
then she would have
quietly helped us.
the only reason
she’s showing us her cards
is to try to gain our trust.
Don: What’s the point
in doing that?
Norman: It’s all so she can get
solid evidence of our rebellion.
In other words,
she’s in a position
where the higher-ups
won’t trust her
unless she has proof.
She doesn’t have the power
to ship us out like mom does.
- Gilda: Evidence?
- ( Don gasps ) Wait.
What happens if she finds
the rope we hid in the tree?!
norman: It’s fine.
Explaining the rope is easy.
We can say we were gonna use it
for a game, but if we--
ray: If she finds the tools
to break the trackers,
then we’re done for.
Norman: That kind of evidence
would be hard to explain.
( Don and gilda gasp )
Ray: No need to worry.
I’m not gonna let that happen.
I’m not finished
making it yet, anyway.
Norman: That won’t be an issue
if we can convince her
that we don’t know where
they are or how to break them.
I’m sure sister krone
would believe us
if we play our cards right.
Gilda: You’re going to her room?
you’re dealing
with sister krone here.
it’s nice she offered
to give us information, but--
don: Hang on.
Why are we cooperating with her?
Does it give us an advantage?
Norman: If we
use her effectively,
we might learn something useful.
additionally,
it’ll keep her out of the way
so we can focus
on the inspection.
( Don sighs )
( Grunts )
( Gilda sighs )
Emma: We’ll be fine.
we have to use
every opportunity that we can!
( Laughs )
( Gilda sighs )
( Norman chuckles )
- ( Don sighs )
- ( Norman grunts )
Don: Hmm.
Norman: Ray, can I talk to you?
I want to discuss
the investigation.
Ray: Okay.
( Door opens )
( Door closes )
Emma: I have a favor
I want to ask of you guys.
( Clock ticking )
( Tape rips )
( Both grunt )
( Footsteps approaching )
( Both sigh )
( Door creaks )
♪
Krone: We’re allies now,
so ask me anything.
( Both gasp )
Krone: Hmm?
( Emma grunts )
Norman: We can ask
whatever we want?
Krone: Yes. It can be about
the farm or even headquarters.
( Clock ticking )
- Norman: Then...
- Emma: Show it to us,
the thing that receives signal
from our trackers.
Krone: Ohh.
( Chuckles )
Oh. Of course.
There’s not a lot to it,
is there?
It shows the current location,
but doesn’t say who it is.
( Both sigh )
Krone: So you knew that there
were tracking devices?
norman: Yeah.
We found out from mom,
but we don’t know where they are
or how to destroy them.
Emma: Do you know, sister?
krone: Yes.
They’re found in your ear.
( Both gasp )
Krone: Around here, on the left.
( Both sigh )
Krone: Hmm.
I don’t really know
how to break them,
but I do know that,
if they’re broken,
it notifies
the tracking tool and hq,
♪
You’d either have to take it out
or just cut that part off.
norman: How?
There are no sharp blades here.
Krone: There is one, a scalpel.
norman:
There’s no medicine outside,
and I don’t
wanna start our escape
with blood loss or infections.
Krone: The infirmary
has medicine
and anesthesia you could use,
tools as well.
Now, the supplies should last
at least five kids.
I can teach you how to use them.
I’ll even lend you the key.
Since that’s settled,
anything else?
( Both sigh )
Emma: How old are you, exactly,
and have you
always been a product?
Krone: Mm-mm-mm.
It’s pretty rude of you
to ask a lady her age,
but i’m gonna
let it slide this time.
I’m 26. I was born and raised
at this house,
though not here
at plant three, mind you.
Norman: There’s more than one?
Krone: And from what
I saw in the records,
it seems isabella’s 31.
norman: Tell me,
have you seen the outside?
- Krone: Not once.
- ( Both gasp )
Krone: Oh? Did you think
that i’d lie and say yes?
- I haven’t.
- ( Norman sighs )
Krone: But there are
humans out there.
The higher-ups and us adults
make all the food
that you kids eat.
However, there are humans
who bring your clothes
and supplies from outside.
I’ve seen them
at headquarters once,
and it seemed like they were
all in equal standing
with each other.
What you all need to do
is get mixed in
with the humans
who won’t get eaten.
( Both sigh )
Emma: So just how long...
Have the demons been around?
Krone: "Demons"?
Oh, you must mean them.
Emma: And how did
the world get like this?
If you know.
Krone: I don’t.
( Emma gasps )
( Norman sighs )
Emma: Where is
this house located?
Krone: No idea.
Norman: What about the security?
Krone: Now, that, I know.
There isn’t too much.
they rely
on the tracking devices,
so there aren’t
many guards posted.
I doubt they even patrol.
( Emma grunts )
Norman: Thank you
for all your help.
Krone: Is that it?
Norman: Yeah. Have a good night.
( Krone chuckling )
( Both gasp )
( Krone laughing )
So you already knew
where the trackers were
and how to break them!
I’m actually impressed.
i’ve learned
a lot of interesting things
- during our talk tonight.
- ( Both gasp )
Krone: Info can be provided
without words.
Humans tend to give away
a lot of information,
even if they’re
just standing there.
Blinking, gaze,
sweating, attitude,
gestures, pupils, and pulse,
they all hint at what
you’re really thinking.
What gave it away
was when I said
the tracking device
was located in your ear
and neither of you
even bothered to check.
Then when you found out
how to remove them,
you didn’t look
the least bit happy about it.
♪ So why did you ask
♪ when you already found out
all on your very own? ♪
Is there something
you want to hide from me?
i bet there’s a secret
you’re all keeping, isn’t there?
( Giggles )
Anyway, have you
heard of the one?
( Both gasp )
( Krone chuckles )
I bet that you haven’t.
Do you want to know?
i’ll save that
for your next visit here,
so come back anytime,
and we can talk much more
than we did today.
( Clock ticking )
Ray: Hey, mom.
( Camera clicks )
I see.
So nothing shows up here
at first.
Isabella: Your last reward
is a camera, huh?
Ray: I was just curious
about how these things work,
since i’ve only
ever seen photographs
and cameras in books.
If I were greedy, I would have
wanted to develop them.
( Gasps )
wow. It looks like
you froze a moment in time.
About that other thing,
can it wait ’til after lunch?
Isabella: Yes.
That should be fine.
( Door closes )
♪
( Clock ticks )
( Clock striking 12:00 )
Well, then...
i think
it’s about time to begin.
( Children chattering )
( Camera clicks )
( Ray gasps )
( Sighs )
Let’s review.
During the free time
we have after eating lunch,
i’m gonna be distracting mom.
meanwhile, you two
will inspect above the wall.
don and gilda,
stand outside where you can see
the second-floor window
to the south.
- ( Both gasp )
- Ray: Stay alert.
i’ll signal to you
if i’m not able distract mom,
and that’s when you two
tell the others
to cancel the inspection.
( Both grunt )
Ray: According
to our original plan,
there are six days left,
but we have the 2 1/2 months
’til I get shipped out.
So, if things go wrong,
we can bail.
We do everything in secret
and pretend to be controllable.
( Both grunt )
Mark: Don!
You should come play with us!
- Naila: Gilda, too!
- Don: Sure!
- Are you ready to play tag?
- ( Children laughing )
Norman: Ray, we need to talk.
Ray: What?! Krone found out
that we can break
the tracking devices?
( Both grunt )
Norman: We should
move up the escape.
How soon can you break them?
( Ray gasps )
( Sighs )
( Both gasp )
- ( Norman chuckles )
- Emma: What even was that?
Ray: With this, i’ve got
all the pieces that I need.
I can break them whenever.
( Emma chuckles )
( Ray laughs )
Emma: Hmm?
Ray: Look at your face.
- Emma: Hey!
- ( Ray chuckles )
norman: This is quite
a double-edged sword, isn’t it?
Are we going to break
the tracking devices
and escape first, or is krone
going to find the evidence
and turn us in before we
have a chance to do that?
( Emma sighs )
Ray: Don’t worry. I handled it.
( Chuckles )
( Clock ticking )
Krone: Hmm. I wonder...
Why did they pretend
not to know anything?
They knew exactly
where the devices were
and how to destroy them.
But how did they even
find out in the first place?
actually,
how will they break them?
Are they going to use
a specific tool?
Could they have made
something to do that?
if that’s the case,
it could be the evidence I need.
Is that why they were scared
and lied to me?
Well, then, guess it’s time
to start searching. ( Chuckles )
( Overlapping chatter )
Child: Can’t wait
to go outside and play.
Krone: Now’s my chance.
( Laughs )
( Humming a tune )
( Grunting )
( Groans )
Phil: Huh?
( Krone sighs )
- Phil: Hey, what are you doing?
- ( Krone gasps )
( Phil chuckles )
( Krone giggles )
I’m cleaning
the floors in here.
Phil: Oh.
( Laughs )
( Krone grunts )
( Gasps )
♪
( Panting )
- ( Norman sighs )
- ( Emma gasps )
( Ray chuckles )
Krone: Found it.
It’s true.
How could something
like this not be?
( Laughs )
How unexpected! Now I have
isabella’s second weakness!
( Giggles )
well, then,
how should I make my next move?
If I show this note to grandma
and appeal to her,
can I overthrow Isabella?
Her position as mom
will finally be mine!
( Giggles )
Once that happens,
I can ship out
those brats, too.
Wait a sec. But how does ray
even know about this?
Because Isabella herself
shouldn’t be aware of it.
- ( Knock on door )
- ( Gasps )
( Knock on door )
( Gasps )
( Woman vocalizing )
( Winces )
( Exhales )
isabella:
It’s from headquarters.
You should open it.
( Vocalizing continues )
( Paper crinkling )
- ( Krone gasps )
- Isabella: It’s unfortunate,
but that’s how it is.
This is goodbye.
( Krone shudders )
♪
( Mechanical laugh )
( Singing in Japanese )