Emma: Conny?
( Footsteps echoing )
( Gasps )
( Demon hisses )
( Emma gasps )
( Panting )
( Children snoring )
( Clock ticking )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
( Thunder rumbling )
( Children chattering )
Child: Good morning!
Boy: Good morning!
Girl: Hey, Phil,
no running in here!
Boy: And this goes there?
- Isabella: Yes, that’s right.
- ( Emma gasps )
Isabella: Can you finish
setting the table, Mark?
Mark: Sure thing, mom!
( Isabella chuckles )
( Emma gasps )
( Footsteps approaching )
Norman: Hi, Emma. Morning.
( Emma stammers )
Norman: Come on. Smile.
( Emma gasps )
Norman: Listen, Emma.
we have to act
like nothing happened.
Sure, we might have
broken the rules
by going to the gate last night,
but that doesn’t mean
we saw anything.
Emma: But we left
little bunny there.
Norman: That’s right, and we
have to assume mom found it,
but that
doesn’t tell her anything
about who left it behind.
Emma: Mom was laughing
at breakfast.
She doesn’t show it
on her face at all.
Norman: And that’s
what we have to do, too.
Otherwise, she’ll notice
that something is wrong.
We can’t let that happen,
so smile.
( Emma whimpers )
The delicious food,
the white clothes
that show when we’re dirty,
our regulated lives,
all of it is to keep up our
quality of life as merchandise.
The only thing left for us to do
is wait while we’re
shipped out randomly.
Norman: But the demon
confirmed it wasn’t random.
He said, "another six-year-old.
they’ve all
been average lately."
Emma: What’s it mean?
Norman: Based on what
the demons said,
our ages determine
their grades of meat,
and if I remember correctly,
the siblings
who were shipped out before
were all between 6 and 12,
and if six years old
is ranked as normal,
then the highest quality
must be...
Emma: Twelve years old!
But what about our scores?
Meat won’t start tasting better
because of how well it did
on some test, will it?
norman: True.
The results weren’t announced
unless we received
full marks, which means...
( Emma gasps )
The shipping order?!
Norman: Yeah. When we turn six,
we’re harvested in order
from lowest test scores up,
and once we’ve reached
the age of 12,
it seems we get shipped out,
no matter what.
Emma: So we were exempt from it
because we got
perfect scores on our test?
Norman: But I
still don’t get it.
Why do our scores
dictate the order?
Emma: And why do you think
being between 6 and 12
is what matters?
Is it the size of our bodies?
can’t be, or else
weight would be a factor.
( Norman sighs )
( Gasps )
It’s our brains.
( Emma gasps ) That means...
Norman: That the brain
must taste the best,
and the more developed it is,
the better.
Emma: They eat brains?
Norman: Seems so,
and they’ll
spend a lot for them,
which makes us
valuable merchandise.
Remember the order?
Conny was shipped most recently.
Before her was hao
and Sadie before him.
Following the cycle
they’ve used so far,
the next shipment should be
at least two months from now,
which means you and I
need to come up with a way
for all of us to escape
from here before then.
( Emma grunts )
( Thunder rumbling )
Norman: We’ll start by making
a rudimentary map of the site.
The house is in the middle,
lined up with the gate,
and the forest encircles
the rest of the property.
so which exit
do we choose for our escape,
the gate or the forest?
Emma: I’d say the forest.
The gate’s always closed,
except for when
they’re shipping,
and when it’s open...
Norman: Those demons are there.
So when do we try to escape?
During the day at playtime
when we’re able to get
out of the house freely,
or during shipping, when mom’s--
Emma: We can’t wait
to do it during shipping!
That plan means
someone we love dies!
Norman: You’re right.
And i’m also worried
the younger ones won’t be able
to stay awake during the night.
It’s decided.
We’ll escape during the day
through the forest,
if that’s possible.
Emma: That depends
on what things are like
beyond the forest.
( Both panting )
( Norman grunts )
Emma: Huh.
- ( Thumping )
- Huh?!
Uh, what are you doing?!
- ( Norman yelps )
- ( Emma gasps )
Norman! Are you okay?
( Norman shudders )
I guess I must be tired
from thinking too much.
( Emma chuckles )
All right. Guess it’s up to me.
( Grunting )
( Norman chuckles )
So, is something there?
Emma: Nothing.
the wall looks
about two or three meters thick.
The top of it
is pretty high up.
Norman: But there are no guards.
It’s quiet.
Emma, what do you think?
Emma: It was built sturdy.
i don’t see
any rough edges or seams,
and the surface is smooth.
there’s no way
someone could climb this.
norman: Then,
should we just give up?
That’s what it’s meant
to make us think,
but if it was you or me,
climbing this wouldn’t be
a problem with a rope.
Norman: I don’t sense
any demons.
Only mom’s watching us.
So there’s no need
to be scared.
Emma: Hmm.
( Bell tolling )
( Overlapping chatter )
Girl: Huh? There’s two missing.
Mark: Mom! ( Crying )
Isabella: What’s wrong?
Did something happen?
Mark: I’m sorry! I lost naila
while we were
playing in the forest!
i looked,
but I couldn’t find her!
( Sobbing )
( Norman gasps )
Isabella: No need to worry.
Everyone stay here
’til I get back.
I won’t be long.
Mark: I’m sorry.
( Thunder rumbling )
♪
- ( Paul gasps )
- ( Overlapping chatter )
Girl: She found her.
Phil: Mom!
Mark: Naila!
( Children laughing )
Isabella: She got tired
and fell asleep. See?
She’s perfectly fine.
Mark: I was worried!
( Children laughing )
Mark: I’m sorry, naila!
Norman: How did she do that?
It’s almost like she knew
exactly where naila was.
Emma: Well, actually,
now that you mention it,
mom’s always been really good
at finding us.
She found us quickly,
no matter where we hid.
Norman: Wait.
That’s not a watch.
- It’s a tracker.
- ( Emma gasps )
Norman: Then that probably means
we have a chip inside us.
She did that on purpose,
pulled out her "watch"
so we’d see and figure it out.
That must be mom’s way
of telling us,
"no matter who you are,
I won’t let you escape."
Child: Better be ready.
( Overlapping chatter )
Norman: So mom is...
Emma: Our enemy.
( Thunder rumbles )
norman: First,
we’ve gotta get some rope.
I might have an idea
where to look.
we’ll meet up
in the hallway at 10:00.
Emma: Wait!
if they have
tracking devices on us,
then what if there are cameras
or listening devices also?
Norman: Don’t worry.
I already took a look around.
There’s nothing like that here.
Emma: Wait. You did?
norman: Yeah,
but I wouldn’t have guessed
that the security measures
aren’t located on the building.
They’re on us.
- ( Thunder rumbling )
- Emma: Norman...
Do you think mom already knows
we went all the way to the wall?
Norman: I doubt it.
When we tried to deliver
little bunny,
it didn’t seem
like she knew we were there.
Emma: That’s good.
Norman: That tells us
mom doesn’t know where we are
at any given time.
She can only tell our location
when she checks.
What she does know is that
someone other than conny
brought little bunny
to the gate that night.
However, I don’t think
she’s figured out who yet.
Otherwise, she wouldn’t have
warned us so indirectly.
Emma: That makes sense.
Don: Oh! Hey, Norman!
Do you have a second?
The clock in our room
is busted or something.
Norman: Sure thing.
I’ll be right there.
It’ll be fine, Emma.
She has no reason
to suspect us.
( Thunder rumbling )
Emma: Conny.
Norman: Em--( Gasps )
( Emma gasps )
♪
Isabella: What’s wrong, Emma?
You’re looking a bit pale.
( Norman shuddering )
Isabella: Something happen?
I noticed earlier
that you weren’t
your cheery self.
Emma: Oh, you think so?
♪
Don’t worry about me.
I just got a little sad
thinking about
how i’m gonna have to leave
the house pretty soon.
Isabella: Do you
like living here?
Emma: I love the house
and you, too!
( Norman sighs )
emma: I wonder
what conny’s up to right now.
( Norman gasps )
Emma: You know what?
She said she wanted to be
a loving mother just like you
when she grows up.
Isabella: Yes, I remember.
Conny will become
a lovely young woman
and a good mother, too.
ray: Food’s done.
Time to wash up for dinner.
( Overlapping chatter )
Isabella: I’ll be there soon.
Norman: Let’s go, Emma.
Emma: Mm-hmm.
Isabella: About last night,
did you two go to the gate?
Norman: To the gate?
But that’s against the rules.
Besides, we were tired from
playing tag yesterday. Right?
Emma: That’s right.
Norman: Why do you ask?
Isabella: Never mind,
as long as you didn’t go.
( Both laugh )
( Emma gasps )
( Norman gasping )
( Thunder rumbling )
( Emma panting )
Norman: Can you get up?
( Emma sighs )
( Norman chuckles )
( Insects chirping )
( Door creaks )
( Emma grunts )
( Chain creaking )
( Birds chirping )
emma: You know,
this was a great idea, Norman,
swiping spare tablecloths.
Norman: These can be tied up
and used as rope.
Emma: Now we have a way
to climb over the wall.
Norman: But we still have
to figure out the hard part.
emma: How to deal
with the tracking devices.
Norman: And how to take
everyone else when we escape.
- Emma: Hey, Norman.
- Norman: Hmm?
Emma: I think
it’d be a good idea
to tell ray and get his opinion.
Norman: I was thinking
the very same thing.
I also think ray would be
the least likely to panic.
And because he knows a lot,
he’s good
at working with machines.
He would be an asset
to our plan, but...
Emma: But what?
Norman: Tell you what.
I’ll talk to ray myself.
Why don’t you head back
to the house for now,
- and--
- ray: Why not now?
Emma: Ray!
Ray: Yo.
Hey, sorry. I followed you.
- Emma: Huh?!
- ( Norman chuckles )
Ray: It’s been
bugging me all day,
so I thought I should
just come out and ask you.
Tell me what happened
at the gate the other night.
- Emma: Huh?
- Norman: Mm...
Ray: You know, when you tried
to take little bunny to conny.
You both were acting
a lot weirder than usual
and came back empty-handed,
even though you didn’t see her.
- Norman: You’re so sharp!
- Emma: Uh--
ray: So I assume something must
have happened! Now spill it!
emma: Oh, wow.
Aren’t you a clever one?
( Children chattering,
laughing )
Ray: Demons, huh? A farm.
Mom is the enemy?
This is bad.
Emma: He catches on fast!
Ray: So that means,
this whole time,
mom’s been taking care of us
and feeding us so well
so we can get shipped out
and become demon food.
Emma: Actually, i’m surprised
you’re ready to believe this
so easily.
ray: Huh?
Of course I believe it.
Norman would never make up
such an unbelievably dumb lie.
He’s not you, Emma.
( Emma gasps, groans )
Ray: So, if we’re really
going to make a break for it,
we need to address
a couple things.
First is the number of kids.
We should narrow it down
to those who can make it.
- Emma: Wait!
- Ray: Hmm?
Emma: We’re leaving here
and taking everyone,
and, to make that happen,
we need you.
( Ray gasps )
Everyone? You’re kidding, right?
There are 37 kids here,
and most of them
aren’t even six years old yet.
There’s mom, demons,
homing beacons.
Those factors
take a bad situation
and make it worse.
You want the impossible.
Emma: I know it’ll be tough,
but I don’t think
it’s impossible!
Ray: It can’t be done.
Emma, you don’t get it, do you?
- Emma: Huh?
- Norman: Ray, hang on.
Ray: Ah, I see.
That’s why you said
you’d talk to me.
But you have to be upfront
about something this grave.
- Emma...
- Emma: Yeah, what?
ray: We can’t just worry
about escaping. It’s not enough.
Emma: What do you mean by that?
Ray: We don’t know
what’s waiting outside
beyond this wall,
but there’s a place
we’re getting shipped to.
The fact that there’s
a farm and a buyer
should give you an idea.
What waits outside
is a demon’s world.
There is no place
for humans to live.
It was never meant for our kind.
( Emma gasps )
Ray: So it’s impossible.
if we take everyone,
then we’ll all die out there.
We leave them behind.
That’s the best option.
Emma: No way.
( Ray gasps )
Emma: Even if it’s impossible,
they’re all coming!
- We can figure it out!
- ray: What?!
Emma: I don’t know
what’s on the outside,
but leaving part of our family
behind isn’t an option!
I want conny to be
the last one they take.
Never again. I won’t
lose anyone else like that.
If there isn’t a place
out there for humans to live,
we’ll carve one out
for ourselves!
together,
we’ll change the world!
- ( Ray gasps )
- Emma: Thank you, ray,
for helping me to understand.
We’re planning an escape
where we get everyone out.
I’m not bending on this.
- I’ve decided.
- ( Ray gasps )
Emma: You have to come to grips
with my plan, ray,
so stop jabbering, and help us!
- ( Ray grunts )
- ( Norman laughing )
Ray: How can you just laugh?
Her plan is suicide!
emma: We’re escaping
with everyone, and that’s it!
I won’t agree to anything else!
I won’t! I won’t! I won’t!
Ray: Someone should
knock some sense into her!
She’s unreasonable!
Norman: Yeah, totally!
i’m glad she’s
her old cheerful self.
Ray: You’re missing
my point, Norman!
Stop her, or you’ll both die!
Of course, you knew all that
from the very start,
didn’t you?
Norman: You didn’t see
the way she cried.
- ( Ray gasps )
- Norman: That night,
I thought she was crying
because she was terrified.
I know now that I was wrong.
what I saw there
made me afraid of dying.
Emma was scared,
but it was the thought
of her family dying
that horrified her.
She’s so amazing,
to be in that situation
and worried
about protecting others.
Ray: But it’s a lost cause!
The three of us could make it,
but trying to take everyone,
it’s like making
a boat out of mud!
( Norman sighs )
Ray: You should be scared.
There’s nothing
to be ashamed of.
don’t let feelings
cloud your vision! We’ll die!
Norman: I do see clearly.
i want to build
a boat out of mud as well!
Ray: Huh? Don’t be a fool!
You’re supposed
to be different!
You’re the coolheaded one
who should weigh out
the best option!
What gives, huh?!
- Norman: Because of Emma...
- ( Ray gasps )
Norman: And how i’d do anything
to always put a smile
on her face.
Ray: You’ve gone crazy.
And what if Emma dies
because of it?
Norman: That won’t happen.
I will make sure of it,
and i’ll do whatever it takes.
Look on the bright side.
I’ve always been able
to accomplish
whatever I set out to do.
If you bake mud,
you can make a vessel,
so a boat that’s made out of mud
wouldn’t necessarily sink.
Ray: You’ve lost your mind.
Norman: You think?
Perhaps Emma and I
are both insane.
We’ve completely lost it,
so you can’t
let us do it alone.
( Ray chuckles )
You jerk.
What kind of friend
would I be if I did?
( Bell tolling )
Emma: Uh, hey, guys,
shouldn’t we still have
some free time left?
Norman: We should go.
( Children murmuring )
- Child: So cute.
- Isabella: Attention.
I want you to meet Carol,
your newest sibling,
and this is sister krone.
She’s here to help me
with my duties.
( Krone giggles )
( Emma gasps ) An adult?
Norman: Another enemy.
Krone: I’ll be living here
with all of you from now on.
It’s nice to meet you.
( Children murmuring greetings )
Child: Nice to meet you.
( Isabella chuckles )
( Clock ticking )
( Norman gasps )
( Emma gasps )
( Clock ticks )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )