( Singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
( Clock ticking )
( Ticking continues )
Emma: I’ve been thinking
this whole time,
"what should I be doing
for norman’s sake?"
And the answer
was to do nothing.
Mom told me to give up
and free myself
of the pain I felt...
But I refuse to ever give up.
I won’t let his death
be in vain.
Will you?
( Ray chuckles )
It seems like both of us
are on the same page, then.
Emma: Let’s run away.
I came to talk about that.
Ray: I wanted to talk, too.
The past two months,
we couldn’t communicate,
since we were worried
mom would see.
Emma: Yeah. I didn’t want her
to know our true intentions,
so I stayed quiet.
Ray: "True intentions"?
emma: Right.
Mom’s really cautious.
Even though the two of us
weren’t doing anything,
she never stopped watching us,
but that’s something
we can use against her.
If she stays focused on me,
then I can keep her eyes
away from the other kids.
( Ray gasps )
Don and gilda, huh?
emma: Yeah.
I left them in charge.
They’re training the others
and making preparations.
Ray: How far along are you?
Emma: It’s all ready.
There’s warm clothing,
supplies, and food.
We can leave whenever.
Ray: That’s impressive,
but how will you escape?
Emma: Oh, don’t worry.
I have it all planned.
Let’s run tomorrow morning,
before you get shipped out.
Ray: Hold it. That’s dangerous.
Things are a lot different now.
The escape should be at night,
when it’s easier to hide.
- ( Emma stammers )
- Ray: Just hear me out.
You should sit down.
♪
okay, then.
There are two problems here.
First, mom’s watchful eyes.
She’s always watching us
and tends to be holding
one of the younger ones
during the day.
and, at night, she puts
the babies to sleep in her room.
In order to make sure
that everyone escapes here,
we’ll have to separate mom
from all the little ones.
- ( Emma grunts )
- Ray: Next thing
is the cliff
that’s past the wall.
We’re not able
to climb down it.
If we’re getting out,
we’ll have to take
the only bridge
that’s available.
I’m sure there’s
already security,
and, once they know we’re gone,
the guards
are going to rush over.
It’s at the edge
of the headquarters.
those monsters are
going to be all over the place.
Knowing that, what will you do?
( Emma grunts )
Ray: I have the answer
right here.
( Emma gasps )
( Metal clatters )
Oil?
Ray: We’ll just
set the house on fire.
Emma: Y-you’re going
to start a fire?
Ray: That’s right.
While mom is distracted,
trying to put it out,
we’ll pretend
to evacuate everyone.
we’ll block the door
to the secret room beforehand
so that mom can’t get in.
Hq will assume it’s only a fire,
so security won’t be tight
on the bridge,
and you can escape easily.
( Emma gasps )
Ray: As a bonus,
I also went ahead
and hid ten molotovs
behind some rocks in the forest.
Emma: Wait. You what?!
Ray: Don’t underestimate
how much i’ve prepared.
Now, when you’re
heading to the bridge,
throw these
into the plants next to ours.
It’ll start another fire,
spreading security
even thinner.
The forest’ll be empty,
since it’s dark,
so no one should die.
( Emma grunts )
Ray: So instead
of leaving tomorrow,
let’s go now.
( Emma gasps )
Can you do it or not?
( Emma sighs )
- Ray: Don’t worry.
- Emma: Huh?
Ray this place is pretty far
from everyone’s rooms.
none of them
should get caught in the fire.
They’ve trained for this,
haven’t they?
What we taught
them during tag--
wait. Is your leg still hurt?
Emma: It’s all healed!
( Thumps )
Ray: Then it’s decided.
Emma: Ray.
Ray: But, to be honest,
i’m still against it,
the whole idea of taking
all the other kids along.
( Splashing )
Especially knowing there’s
a cliff beyond those walls.
what I think is
you should take Don and gilda
and at least leave
the babies here, if anything.
It’s the best thing
for them and for you.
( Emma sighs )
Ray: However,
i already know
you’re not gonna listen.
Though, I guess i’d rather
you do that than not escape,
so I won’t harp on it.
It’s your choice.
( Clock ticking )
( Emma sighs )
Ray: Why are you still here?
Go tell Don and gilda.
Emma: About your plan...
Ray: Hmm?
Emma: We’re throwing molotovs?
ray: Yeah.
Could be you or maybe Don.
( Sighs )
( Emma sighs )
Actually, what i’m
most concerned about
is what if,
when we start the fire,
mom decides to abandon
the whole building?
She might just give up
on putting it out
and focus on us
since we’re the merchandise.
- Ray: Exactly.
- ( Emma sighs )
Ray: There’s a pretty good
chance of that happening.
that’s why simply
starting a fire isn’t enough.
We’ve gotta make sure
we stop her,
’cause there won’t be
an opportunity later.
( Emma sighs )
- Ray: But don’t worry.
- ( Emma gasps )
There’s always this.
( Cap rattles )
( Cap clatters )
♪
( Emma gasps ) Ray!
( Ray chuckles )
Pretty smart thinking, huh?!
I’m gonna burn to ash
on my shipment date.
Mom can’t abandon me.
I’ve been waiting for this day.
I decided this years ago,
and its finally time
to act it out.
This is my retaliation.
- ( Emma gasps )
- Ray: You know, Emma,
when it came
to all that studying,
I was never really into it.
Regardless, I did it
to improve my value,
and I wanted it to be
the highest possible!
For 12 years...
I’ve been the feast that
they’ve all been waiting for.
Tonight, i’m taking that away
right before
the anticipated harvest.
Don’t think you can eat me!
I won’t give you
that satisfaction!
Food? Product? Yeah, right!
This is gonna show them all
that i’m human!
Emma: Ray.
Ray: I have to do this.
It’s the best way, the only way.
i’ve watched so many of
my siblings die over the years.
I used them,
and each one of them
was a good kid.
They were so kind and carefree.
- Emma: Wait!
- Ray: Don’t move.
listen up, Emma.
You only have one chance,
so make this work.
Norman and I gave
our lives for this.
I’m begging you. Don’t waste it.
( Emma gasps )
Ray: Catch.
This is from...
( Gasping )
( Clock chiming )
( Emma gasps )
Ray: I’m finally 12.
It was a life I wanted out of,
but I Cherish the time
I spent with you guys.
- Emma: No! Please don’t!
- Ray: Thanks a lot.
( Emma gasps )
Ray: Nice knowin’ you, Emma.
♪
( Isabella humming lullaby )
( Humming continues )
- ( Clock chiming )
- ( Gasps )
( Pen scratching )
Happy birthday,
dear ray, and goodbye.
- Emma: Ray!
- ( Isabella gasps )
( Sighs )
( Panting )
( Emma sobbing )
( Isabella gasps )
What is this horrible smell?
( Isabella gasping )
Emma: Ray!
Ray!
♪
Emma: No! Ray!
( Isabella gasps ) Ray?
Emma!
Emma: Mom, please, do something!
You have to help ray!
( Isabella gasps )
( Grunts )
Did he set himself on fire?
- Gilda: Mom!
- Isabella: Gilda!
Go get the babies from my room,
and take everyone outside!
- Hurry!
- Gilda: Right!
( Overlapping yelling )
( Children panting )
Isabella: If anything,
I have to save the brain.
Just stay back, Emma!
Emma: Ray.
( Isabella groans )
The sprinklers aren’t working.
What happened?
emma, you need
to get out of here, too!
otherwise,
you’ll end up getting--
what?
Emma?
( Gasps )
( Fire crackling )
( Growls )
Were the children
wearing their shoes?
( Emma panting )
( Boy gasps ) She’s here!
You made it!
( Children laugh )
( Scattered laughter )
Emma: Thanks for waiting, guys!
( Ray gasps )
( Clock chiming )
Thanks a lot.
Nice knowin’ you, Emma.
♪
Emma: Nice catch, huh?
- Ray: What the?!
- Emma: Sorry,
but i’m not letting you die,
and the other kids
aren’t, either.
Ray: Wait. Other kids?
- ( Knock on door )
- ( Gasps )
( Footstep splashes )
Boy: Emma, I brought
what you asked me for!
Boy 2: Yeah, and everyone’s
ready to go now!
Emma: Thanks, you guys.
You were a big help.
( Ray gasping )
- Emma: All right, ray.
- ( Boys laugh )
Emma: Time to change.
( Clock ticking )
( Splash )
( Ray sighs )
Emma: You done?
Then, next is--
ray: Emma, wait.
Listen. I just think--eh?
Are you still planning
on dying, you idiot?!
shut up,
and get ready to run away!
Boys: Hey, Emma! All done here!
Emma: Good.
( Ray gasps )
( Clock ticking )
Ray: What’s this?
Boy 2: Your replacement.
Boy 1: It’ll create
a specific smell.
( Ray gasps ) Those braids...
Emma: Anna gave them to me.
( Ray gasps )
Emma: And now for the tracker.
just give me your ear,
and I can take it out for you.
Ray: Wait a sec.
What are you--
Emma: "If you’re gonna die,
then don’t make it here.
I’ll show you something cool,
so shut up, and follow."
Norman wanted me
to tell you that.
Ray: Huh? Seriously?
Norman: To my dearest Emma,
i’m going to give you
a new plan to follow.
First, ray intends to die.
From what he said, he’s doing it
so that you and I
don’t get killed.
He didn’t include himself
in the numbers.
He’s not escaping.
ray has decided
to die inside this house.
he’s going
to set himself on fire
to distract mom
in order to let us run away.
That’s his entire plan,
but I won’t allow him
to do that, not ever.
that’s why
i’m writing down the plan
I recently came up with for you.
( No audible dialogue )
it’ll happen
in about two months,
probably the night
before ray’s birthday.
using the fire
that he’s planning to start,
I want you to save ray,
outwit mom,
and escape with everyone.
don’t worry.
You have enough time.
by the way,
I got something unexpected...
From sister krone.
♪
I’m counting on you, Emma.
Please, take care of ray
and the rest of our siblings.
Finish what we started.
Emma: Now let’s begin, Norman.
( Breathes deeply )
Ray!
♪
Okay, time to go.
Let’s head for the wall!
Children: Yeah!
Ray: Norman.
( Isabella gasps )
Ray: Hey, Don, what’s happening?
do they all know
about the house’s secret
and the escape
we’ve been planning?
- Don: Yeah.
- Ray: But how?
Don: Everybody
found out from Emma.
Emma: Let’s tell them
about the escape, okay?
( Norman gasps )
Emma: It’s just I have a feeling
that the rest of our siblings
really aren’t as immature
as we think they are.
since we’ll be
running from monsters,
it’s better they know
what dangers lie ahead.
that way,
they can join us willingly.
( Norman grunts )
Emma: And, besides,
mom doesn’t suspect
anyone but the older kids.
Is it reckless?
Norman: Afraid so.
Emma: But we can catch mom
off guard with this plan!
It’s the only way to actually
escape with everyone.
don: We started
by telling four others.
Krone: We’re allies now,
so ask me anything.
Norman: Whatever we want?
Krone: Yes. It can be about
the farm or even headquarters.
Don: Nat, Anna...
Lannion, thoma...
We let them all hear
what sister krone said.
Ray: Since that far back?
Don: It took us two months,
but we managed to bring in
the rest of the kids.
Emma was only pretending
to have given up,
but, the whole time,
she was actually
giving instructions
to everyone.
Mom never even noticed.
emma:
They’re training the others
and making preparations.
Ray: How far along are you?
Emma: It’s all ready.
There’s warm clothing,
supplies, and food.
We can leave whenever.
( Children panting )
Ray: You guys...
( Emma gasps )
Norman.
Hmm.
Nat and I will climb up first.
We’ll help you guys
once we’re at the top.
Don: Hear that? Just do it like
we trained, and you’ll be fine!
Emma: We’re all
gonna escape safely!
- ( Children yell )
- Thoma: All right!
Ray: Hey, wait a sec.
Isabella: Everything is burning,
all of it.
But...
( Laughing )
Ray and Emma,
they’re still alive!
My darlings, I will never
let you escape from here!
( Feet shuffling )
Ray: Is this everyone?
( Isabella gasps )
Phil: Hey, mom...
( Glass shatters )
( Singing in Japanese )