How to approach a cat.
Step one: Don't make eye contact.
Step two: Assume a crouching posture.
That do anything for ya?
You can tell by my body language
that I'm not a threat, right?
Step three: Approach ever so slowly.
This is incredible!
I guess that guy on TV wasn't kidding!
His advice is just what I needed.
Oh, hey! Nishikata!
What were you doing?
Nothing.
Curse you, Takagi!
I was this close to petting
that cat when you came along!
But...
On the other hand, I'm glad she
didn't actually see me petting it.
Because if she did...
Ooh, Nishikata's petting a cat!
I thought boys weren't supposed to like cute things.
She'd never let me live it down!
And there's no way I'm gonna give
her more ammo to tease me with!
Look, a cat.
Really?
Oh, wow. You like cats?
Not especially.
Crap! That was close.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Over here.
So naive, Takagi.
Cats are very wary creatures.
There's no way one would just waltz right--
Come here.
--Wh-What?!
Why? That wasn't even a proper call!
Unless...
What is she, some sort of cat whisperer?
That's a good boy.
You're looking cuter than usual, Meeta.
Wait, you know this cat?
Yep. He belongs to the old lady who
lives around the corner from us.
No wonder! That explains it.
Aww. So soft.
He's great. And he really likes people.
He'll let you pet him all you want.
Could it really be?
The coveted all-you-can-pet cat?
I need him!
Why don't you play with him a little?
What? Why would I?
Come on.
You were trying to pet the other cat.
You used that trick that was on TV yesterday.
I think you wanna.
She already knows!
I just thought that guy on TV didn't
know what he was talking about, so...
So... You don't particularly like cats or anything?
No. Not really.
And I've definitely never
wanted to pet a cat or anything.
Really? That's surprising.
They're just so cute.
Their coats are all fluffy.
And their paws are so squishy.
Are you kidding me?
This cat even lets people touch his paws?
I wanna touch!
But I can't!
I've dug myself too deep for that!
I know!
I really don't get why people are always
going on and on about petting cats.
It's not like they're really that cute.
And even if they were, I wouldn't want to touch them.
When it comes down to it, they're animals.
You can never be sure what they'll do.
You're taking a risk every time you approach one.
I see what's going on.
You're saying that because you're
afraid of getting scratched.
She took the bait!
Of course I'm not afraid!
But... If you don't believe me,
I'll just have to prove it
right now by petting this cat!
That's okay.
I actually believe you now.
Sorry I doubted you.
Your face is like an open book, Nishikata!
You really want to pet this cat, huh?
Takagi!
What'll it be?
You gonna pet him? Or leave him hanging?
I want to pet him.
Is that okay?
Mm-hmm.
Though I think Meeta has different plans.
What do you mean?! He disappeared?!
Yeah. Do you want to go look for a different cat to pet?
We're gonna be late for school.
So I asked, and Satou said
she likes Tanaka from Class 3.
Oh, I called it.
Didn't I call it?
I can't take it anymore!
I want to talk about love!
So I've been doing some thinking.
And I was wondering, what's like your type?
Was that too abrupt?
I never expected you to ask.
I happen to like the dependent type.
As for me, I prefer a well-built physique and long hair.
Oh, yeah?
I never would have guessed.
It's happening!
They're ready to talk about love too!
It's funny.
You just caught us in the middle of discussing that.
Did I really? What a coincidence.
They've both grown so much!
All right. I'm gonna dig deeper here.
What's your type, Yukari?
I'm so glad you asked!
Well, if I had to choose,
I'd say long legs and handsome features are nice.
What about hair?
She's really particular about a guy's hair.
I tend to like longer hair too, like you do.
Ah! This is fun!
I've wanted to have a conversation
like this with friends forever!
So then a borzoi, yeah?
Uh-huh. A borzo--Eh?
I'm sorry, what are you talking about?
Dogs, duh. What are you talking about?
Which breed is your favorite?
I don't know, Chihuahuas?
What? But they don't fit into your description at all!
Well, there are some long-haired Chihuahuas out there.
You gonna draw?
Hm?
You're going to run out of time.
Yeah.
Why does it have to be a portrait?
Can't we just draw whatever we want?
I'm your reference. You have to actually look at me.
I am looking.
Everyone?
Remember to observe your subject.
Don't get too focused on drawing or
this'll take longer than necessary.
You need to strike a balance.
Take twice as much time studying your
reference as you do drawing them.
You heard her.
Yeah, I did.
Why are you laughing?
Oh... Oh, sorry. It's nothing.
Yeah, right.
What was that all about?
Is there something on my face?
No, there wasn't anything there when I checked
in the bathroom mirror during the break.
What, then? Bed head?
No, I checked my hair, too.
Is she just laughing at my face itself?
I can't do anything about that!
Calm down, calm down!
I know.
It's just her usual game.
There's nothing wrong-- she's just making
me worry so she can enjoy my reaction.
Well two can play at that game.
Are you laughing at how bad your drawing is?
I am not!
Then is there something on my
face that's making you laugh?
Ugh!
I didn't expect her to just ask me flat out.
No, there isn't.
Hm?
Oh, good, she backed down.
Mina, I told you a hundred times!
My eyes don't slant that much, you're exaggerating.
But that's how I envision you, so that's how I drew it.
Don't draw what you see in your mind, draw me!
That's it!
This is supposed to be me?
Well, yeah, that's how I envision you.
I can't help it.
That'll teach her.
Okay. Only ten minutes left.
Oh, this is gonna be good.
Hey, Nishikata.
Mind if I take a look?
Nope. Go ahead.
How do you like that?
Oh, no.
Did I take it too far?
I just drew that based on how I envision you, so...
Nishikata.
That face is too much, Takagi!
My stomach hurts already!
If you're gonna draw me weird,
you should draw that face.
Try again. You can do it. Here.
Okay.
If you can't see me well, I can get closer.
Uh, no, no, that's fine, you're good.
'Kay.
When I get a good look at her, Takagi is kinda...
Pre-- Pret--
Pretty--
There. Finished. You see?
So?
Was I really looking sideways that much?
Oh! Forgot something.
Now it's done.
Why'd you add red? It's not like I'm blushing!
Uh, you have been this whole time.
No, I haven't!
It just looks like that. I swear!
Look closely, I'm not!
Oh, not bad.
This card means your wish will more or less come true.
Really? Is that so?
You should totally get your love fortune told too, Mina.
She's good at this.
See? Go for it!
Huh? You say you want me to get my fortune told,
but I know you really just want to get yours done.
What do you mean? You don't know that!
It's obvious.
No, I just wanted Mina to do it!
This really sucks.
I just wanted to go home today.
Nishikata.
What do you want?
Rock-paper-scissors. You up for a match?
What? Why now?
The loser has to buy the winner juice on the way home.
Sound good?
Sorry, but I just found out I have to clean the
classroom after school, so go home without me.
No problem, I'll just wait here for you.
But I don't want to make you sit around.
Okay.
How about if you win, I have to help you clean up?
Why do you wanna play rock-paper-scissors so bad?
I'm just in the mood for it.
All right, I guess it's okay.
Under one condition!
Which is...?
No psychological attacks like telling
me what you're about to choose, okay?
Sure. Fine with me.
That was close.
I don't need a repeat of that day I lost to her
four times in a row because of those tricks.
Now let's do it.
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
I-I won?
This is my first ever victory over Takagi!
Yes! I finally did it! I bet she's super mad!
Well... Guess I'm helping.
She doesn't seem to mind.
Whatever, I don't care. I still won!
I gotta celebrate while I have the chance.
Nishikata?
What is it, Takagi?
Do you believe in fortune telling?
Uh, fortunes? Not really.
Why do you ask?
The girls and I had ours told today.
Oh.
Is that what that deck of cards was earlier?
They're called tarot cards.
Actually, today my tarot reading was about love.
Oh.
Love?
Turned out good.
It said I'll do well with my current crush.
Your current crush?
Good for you, then.
What about you?
Do you have a crush?
Huh? What was that?
I said, "Do you have a crush?"
Nope! I don't! Definitely not!
I see.
Why did she ask me that just now?
Could it be?
Does Takagi... like me?
What's wrong?
It's nothing! Don't worry about it, everything's cool!
Why do I feel so nervous?
Unless... I...
Do I like Takagi?
No, that's just ridiculous.
Oh, by the way, Nishikata.
Yeah? What's up?
The reason I asked if you had a crush
was because I had your tarot reading done, too.
So that's why you asked me that.
Makes sense I guess.
Should have known.
Wait. Am I disappointed?
Yeah. And guess what?
You'll do well with your crush, too.
That'd be great. If you had a crush.
You're blushing.
That's because I'm hard at work cleaning.
Just change the subject.
So what other readings did you have done?
I asked what you'd pick if we
played rock-paper-scissors.
Huh? As in the match I won earlier?
Mm-hmm.
Clearly that didn't work out.
It's just a fortune, not destiny.
I feel stupid for worrying.
Maybe if you didn't believe in
something as silly as fortune
telling, you wouldn't be stuck here, doing half my work!
It came true, though.
Huh? What do you mean? I won that match, didn't I?
Yup. You sure did.
Come on.
Let's get back to cleaning this place up.
Yeah.
Wait, what?
"Critical."
Today's the day.
I'm gonna beat Takagi.
Count on it!
Oh. Hey, Nishikata. Good morning.
Back atcha. Morning.
Somebody's in a good mood today.
Really? You think so?
I'm in a great mood.
You have no idea what's coming your way.
It just so happens that I'm invincible today.
Because according to my horoscope this morning,
I am number--!
Is it your horoscope? Cancer was number one today.
Huh?!
Hold on a second, how do you know I'm a cancer?
I mean, I said happy birthday to you this year, so...
Oh. I forgot. I guess that makes sense.
What, does she read everyone's horoscope every day?
She's crafty.
But she underestimates me.
I bet she doesn't know that in today's
blood-type fortune, I'm also--!
Also, blood type O's number one, too.
Huh?!
Okay, how do you know that I'm blood type O?
I had a feeling that you were.
Just a guess.
She's just too good.
I was the one underestimating her.
You just can't mess with this girl.
But just you wait.
Today I'm invinc--!
Feeling invincible today, aren't you?
Because of what you heard about both of your fortunes?
Ah.
Are you freaking' kidding me?
Well then. I hope something good happens.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
I don't care if you basically read my mind!
I'm lucky as can be today! I'll get you!
Teased fifty times.
Which means I have to do a hundred and fifty push-ups.
Why? This sucks!
Was it stupid of me to get excited just
because I'm supposed to have good fortune?
Ugh...
What's wrong?
Are you upset because nothing special happened?
It's just a silly fortune.
You seemed to believe that tarot
reading you had the other day!
Man, I've spent all day trying to
think of a plan to beat Takagi,
but I couldn't come up with anything worthwhile.
Maybe I should just call it quits for now.
Either my fortune's wrong, or my luck is
that I only got teased fifty times today.
Hey, Nishikata.
Let's walk home together.
Oh. Yeah, sure, why not?
No, I can't let it end like this!
By the way, what exactly did
your fortune say this morning?
Say what? You mean...
That short description they write with your rank?
Mm-hmm.
Uh, let's see.
Something like...
Cancer is in first place.
You'll land a critical hit! Get 'em!
That's right! A critical hit!
Which means I can turn the tables with a single blow!
It all makes sense now!
No matter how many times she teases me today,
if I can get back at her just once, I win!
Never give up hope!
So? "Something like" what?
Uh... I can't seem to remember what it was.
Hey, Nishikata!
That game Fierce Soccer's on sale today!
We're playing' at his house. You in?
Fierce Soccer, huh?
I did want to play that.
But I can't go home without scoring my critical hit!
Then again, I haven't exactly
come up with any sort of plan yet.
No, I should still be able to do it.
I'm the luckiest man on earth today!
I can do anything!
You regret it?
Turning 'em down?
Oh, that. Nah.
I wanted to walk home with you, anyway.
Hmm. There's gotta be something.
Hold on!
I didn't just say something super awkward, did I?
Uh... I remembered my fortune which said
I'd land a critical hit today, so...
I thought today was gonna be my best
chance to beat you at something!
So what I just said wasn't what it sounded like!
This is the worst!
I didn't land a critical hit!
I scored on my own goal!
So uh... Do me a solid.
Could'ya pretend you didn't hear that?
I guess I can do that.
I'll pretend I heard nothing.
If you say it one more time.
I am not gonna say it again!
Forget you, I'm going this way!
I'll see you around!
A critical hit.
How terrifying.
" Cat "
"Taste"
"Portrait"
"Fortune Telling"