All right, buddy,
I'm sure you know,
but you've been way too loud during class lately.
I expect you to shape up.
Uh. Yes, sir.
Sorry about that
So I'm putting you in charge of
cleaning the science room after school.
Huh?
Don't forget to wipe the desks down, too.
Huh?!
It's not fair that it's just me.
Takagi should be getting punished, too.
She's the one who's always teasing me during class.
But I guess the problem is
that my reactions are too loud.
Let's just get this over with and head--
What are you doing hiding in the closet?
I was trying to scare you.
Ahh...
That was so worth having to waste time in there.
Wait. Lemme guess, you have to clean as punishment, too?
Why don't we just get it over with?
Okay?
So, I have a proposal for you.
Before we start,
let's make a game out of cleaning, so it's more fun.
A game?
Yep.
How about we do rock-paper-scissors,
and the loser has to clean a quarter of the room?
You in?
Hold on.
That means if I win all four times,
I won't have to clean anything!
Heh! Sure.
All right, let's get started.
Round one!
I'll use rock.
Why's she telling me what she's gonna choose?
Rock. So if I go with paper, I'll win?
But she knows that, so--!
I told you I was going with rock.
I hate you!
You need to trust me more.
I won't be tricked twice.
I'll take her word for it next time.
Oh!
And I'm not gonna tell you what I'm picking anymore.
Man.
I knew it.
She's messing with me again.
Hmm?
Nishikata!
Uh. Hey, Nakai!
What's going' on in here?
You two just felt like hanging' out?
No, I was loud in class,
so I have to clean the room as punishment.
Hm. That's rough, man.
What about you?
Me? I'm, uh...
...just hanging' around.
You know.
Oh. Okay.
Hey, Nakai.
Let's not get in their way, yeah?
Oh. You're right.
Well, we'll be on our way.
Cool. See yah around.
Oh, and Nishikata.
Huh?
Good luck to yah, dude!
Uh. Oh, right.
With this?
Come on, let's just get out of here.
Sorry, Takagi!
Mm-hm.
See yah!
By the way, bet you didn't know.
They're going out.
Wait, what? They are?
Seriously? I had no idea.
I mean, I did notice them hanging
out a lot lately, but still...
It's not like they're trying to hide it.
It's just that they're both the kind
of people who wouldn't announce it.
True.
He said he's hanging around, and she was with him.
But if you notice,
they were on their way to the rooftop.
The... The rooftop?
And right about now,
they're probably all alone up there.
Huh? Just the two of them?
You gonna clean?
Huh? Uh. Yeah!
I am.
Aww. Enjoying their time.
With each other.
Up there together.
I wonder what--
I wonder what it's like.
Up there.
Right?
Yeah. I guess so.
Hey. I finished.
Okay, then.
Rock, paper, scissors.
How did I end up losing every time?
Well, that's finally done!
Let's go. It's getting late.
So casual.
I hope you learned your lesson
and won't tease me in class now.
I guess.
I could always just be more discreet.
We're gonna get in trouble no matter what!
Yeah, well, if it happens, it happens.
Not to mention.
I wasn't even told to clean in the first place.
Huh? You've gotta be kidding!
Okay, for real.
Why am I the only one who gets in trouble all the time?
So you're just here to mess with me, like usual?
There's that, but...
...I wanted to enjoy my time, too.
Huh? Enjoy...
...your time?
And on that note,
you're buying me juice on our way home.
What? Why?
The sun's killing me.
Yeah, me too.
I'm really thirsty.
Oh! I know.
How about a competition and the loser buys drinks.
Yeah, why not?
Can I decide what we compete in then?
Think I've got a good idea.
The high bar?
Uh-huh. Whichever one of us can't do a
kickover on the high bar is the loser.
I just happened to try doing a
kickover on the high bar recently.
And bam! I was actually able to
for the first time in my life!
Ever since then, I've been itching' for
my chance to show Takagi up in a duel!
To be honest, I wouldn't be all that
surprised if she could do one, too.
But!
Hey, Nishikata.
You realize, I'm wearing a skirt, right?
Exactly!
Can't flip over the bar wearing a skirt!
She's unable to compete!
I win!
Oh, well.
I call dibs on going first, then.
Eh?
Really? You want to?
Yeah, it's fine.
However, I'd like to add one extra rule.
You can't watch me.
Huh?
You're surprised?
I am wearing a skirt.
So if you look at me on my turn, then you're the loser.
Here I go!
Okay.
Your turn, show me what you got.
Did she really do it?
I have no way of knowing.
Whatever, now's not the time.
I've gotta focus on the task at hand!
Whoa.
Well, we both were able to do it.
So what now?
One more time. Do over.
All right.
Then I'll go first again, 'Kay?
No hesitation.
That's not a good sign.
She's either really confident or hiding something.
I bet she's not even doing a kickover.
She said I lose if I look during her turn.
But it's a different story if she's cheating.
Today's the day that I finally beat her!
No way!
She's actually doing it?
Shorts?!
I'm done.
You can turn around now.
What's wrong?
Sorry, Takagi.
I lose.
Here.
Thanks.
Though, I don't really feel like a winner.
Since you disqualified yourself and all.
Yeah, about that.
If you had shorts on the whole time,
then why didn't you let me watch you do it?
Pervert.
Hey, don't get the wrong idea!
I just wanted to make sure you were
actually swinging over the bar!
Really?
Yes, really!
All right, then.
So you thought I was cheating, is that it?
What?! No, I just... Ugh...
All right, what's the big idea?
Why are you always picking on me, day in and day out?
It's nothing.
Huh? Ba-dump!
Be straight. You like being treated this way, don't you?
Ahh... Squeal!
I said,
"You like being treated this way, don't you?"
Ahh... Squeal!
100% Unrequited Love is so good!
Pay attention, this part's important.
And you can bet it's gonna be on the test.
So make sure you remember it.
Morning. Sorry I'm late.
Hey, Nishikata.
I wasn't expecting you. I thought you were out sick.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah. I think so.
Morning. You have a cold?
Yeah.
But it's nothing.
I can handle it.
No big deal.
Nailed it!
Huh?
I bet you just stayed up watching 100% Unrequited Love.
How did she figure that out?
Squeal, squeal!
Don't say that so loud, it's embarrassing!
Funny, I only heard you screaming.
You're right. Sorry, sir!
Come on, that was really low, Takagi.
You okay?
You're coughing.
Yeah. It's not that bad.
Man.
She won't pull any punches even when I'm sick!
Heh...
But luckily, I have the ultimate
plan to defeat her today!
Wait, what's a guy like him doing here?
Him and his perfect hair!
Now I'm really mad!
I'm going to give him a piece of my mind!
Hey!
Oh wow.
You're so cute.
Squeal!
I can do that!
I may have caught a cold, but it was worth
it for the invaluable knowledge I've gained!
Okay, Takagi. Come at me.
Gimme your best shot!
I'll counter it and make you blush!
Ni--
Come on!
Whenever you're ready!
Uh...
Uh. What?
Don't worry. 'S nothing.
Weird.
She isn't making her move.
I can't stay in this pose forever.
And my right hand's on my chin,
so I can't even take notes.
Wait, what if she figured it out because of the pose?
Is it too obvious I've got a
counter-trap ready to spring on her?
One way to find out.
Sit normally.
What's her deal today?
I don't understand!
Any other day, she'd have teased me three times by now!
Is she sick or something?
Huh?
When she's quiet, she's really...
Uh-oh.
I think I'm starting to second guess my plan here.
Countering with "You're cute," when she
messes with me might be embarrassing.
Duh, of course it is!
How did I ever think I'd be able to say that?
I bet it's because I'm sick,
and didn't get any sleep last night.
Are you okay?
Hey.
Uh. Yeah.
It's all good.
Your face is a little red.
Huh?
And you look tired.
Sure you're good?
Yes, I'm fine.
But you're getting even redder.
Do you have a fever?
Why are you being so nice to me today, Takagi?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm totally okay!
Really?
Really!
When I said I was feeling sick,
it was more like an excuse, anyway.
I really just woke up at like,
eight-thirty, so that's why I was late.
I'm fine! Promise!
Okay.
I guess I believe you.
It's about time!
So... I can tease you again.
Huh? What do you mean?
And of course, she ended up making
fun of me more than usual that day.
Young love!
Squeal!
Yukari, Sanae, what's with the snail's pace?
Power walk, let's go!
Why should I exert myself that much for a Popsicle?
'Cus, it's the baked sweet potato flavor!
It's a summer exclusive!
That's a weird flavor for summer.
They're sold out of it everywhere that I've looked.
But I think this one snack store will have it.
So we gotta check before they sell out too!
What are you doing?
There's no point in taking a shortcut if
you're gonna drag your feet the whole time!
I just noticed Takagi and
Nishikata are inside the store.
Oh hey. You're right.
Could it be that those two are...?
Mina, maybe we shouldn't get in their way--
Hey! Takagi!
Sha-bam!
Got my sweet potato pop!
Uh. I'm happy for you.
See you tomorrow.
They're so lucky.
Lucky how?
Well, look at the two of them.
You know.
A guy and a girl together.
It's just nice.
Huh? Why?
You didn't notice?
Don't blame me, it was your idea.
Hey. Why exactly are we following them?
We live in the opposite direction.
Shhh!
They're gonna notice us. Shut up!
Just tell me what you think.
Don't you feel,
I dunno, like something's going on between them?
Hmm...
Oh! They've got a bike right there!
They should be riding it together, right?
That is so romantic!
Riding home together after school.
Oh, but that's a tough decision, because you can
spend a lot more time together if you walk instead!
Maybe if you trade off every other day?
Can I have a bite of that?
Uh. Yeah, but just one bite, okay?
Hey, Takagi.
You wanna race somewhere?
Are you challenging me?
Uh-huh!
We'll start once we turn that corner.
The first one to make it all the way to the shrine wins.
Hmm. Okay, why not?
Haha. She either has to ride her bike or pull it.
With that flat tire, she'll lose either way.
You have way too wild an imagination!
I guarantee you they're not talking about a race!
They're talking about something more intimate than that.
I just know it!
Nishikata.
I'm up for us racing to the shrine.
But before that...
Hmm?
They're gone?
Did they make it all the way to the shrine already?
No way!
Maybe they realized we were tailing them.
Ugh, come on, let's go home already.
Uh. Yeah.
I say we buy more popsicles on the way.
Will you let me have a bite?
Just buy your own if you're gonna keep eating mine!
So close.
Hmm?
Ah. Did we lose them?
Any idea why they were following us in the first place?
No.
Hey, uh...
Now that I think about it,
we should have gone around that corner too.
It would have been a lot easier to hide over there.
Huh.
I hadn't thought about that, guess you're right.
But I wonder...
Would you have preferred if we did?
Well, no.
It doesn't really matter.
Good!
I'm glad.
Oh, I almost forgot!
We're racing to the shrine, yeah?
Ready, set go!
Huh?! Hey, hold on!
I'm calling' you out!
That's a false start, Takagi!
Tailing those two turned out to be kinda fun in the end.
Taking' the long way home.
They probably did notice us following them.
I better apologize to Takagi tomorrow.
They're out of the baked sweet potato flavor!
It's okay!
They got red bean soup!
What is with you wanting these flavors in the summer?
So you gonna let me have a bite?
"Cleaning Duty"
"Kickover"
"Cold"
"Tailing"