[DEPARTMENT]
What sort of merchandise
are you in the market for?
A getaway car? A safe house?
Or perhaps some
monetary exchange?
Don't worry, I'm not going
to ask why you want it.
Just tell me exactly
what you need.
[ACCELERATOR] Mr.
spells-his-name-"General-Goods"
but-calls-himself-Department,
is that for sale, too?
[DEPARTMENT]
Hmm, is that your only interest?
Because unfortunately,
she's not an option.
She's more of a punching bag.
What's this?
[ACCELERATOR]
It's cash up front.
I got stuck with a crappy job,
and now I'm pissed off.
[DEPARTMENT sighs]
I'm telling you right now,
killing her would cost
you seven million.
I don't understand why
you're so interested
in the girl, anyway.
Oh, goodness, there seems
to be some confusion.
I apologize for not
making myself very clear,
but you see, she's not
the one I just purchased.
It's you, Mr. Department.
[ACCELERATOR]
All right, the job is complete.
I hope you know it's crap
like this that bores me
to tears.
Need? I'm gonna need a team.
To collect this pile
of flesh so I don't puke
every time I inhale.
Can you also look around
and see if there are any
spare clothes that
would fit a female?
What size? How should I know?
Why don't you just make
sure the recovery team
is made up of women.
I'm being very serious.
If there's even one
man among them,
I'll kick his nuts in.
All right, that's it.
You're free to go live your
life however you want to.
Always remember it's up to you
whether you succeed or fail.
Wait, who are you?
[ACCELERATOR] I'm a villain.
Just a punk-ass villain.
[LAST ORDER] "So anyway,
today's supper is going to be
hamburger stew,"
says Misaka Misaka
as she delivers the results
of her scouting report.
[ACCELERATOR] I guess
Yomikawa finally figured out
how to use the rice cooker
to make something
besides rice.
[LAST ORDER] "You said we would
see each other this weekend,
right?" asks Misaka Misaka,
requesting a confirmation.
[ACCELERATOR]
Yeah, unless my plans change.
[LAST ORDER] "Oh! Yomikawa is
bringing the hamburger stew!"
exclaims Misaka Misaka
giving a priority-one report!
Is that so?
Your life is just one pit-stop
after the other, isn't it?
[phone ringing]
[LAST ORDER]
"Is something the matter?"
asks Misaka Misaka,
cocking her head at the sound
of the phone.
[ACCELERATOR]
Nothing to worry about.
Just room service
checking back in.
[LAST ORDER]
"Are you going to be okay?
I don't like you
getting into danger,"
says Misaka Misaka,
pleading with you.
[ACCELERATOR]
Don't be ridiculous.
No need to be
concerned about a guy
you couldn't even
kill with a nuke.
Those maids are proof
that times have taken
a turn for the better,
am I right?
[grunts]
It's insulting for you
to call someone like that
a professional maid.
Yeah? How so?
They're misrepresenting
real maids.
It's not fair that
I get leering looks
just because I wear this outfit.
You want to know
what's not fair?
The fact that unsexy
maids even exist at all!
How's that supposed
to make me feel?
It sounds like I'm going
to have to be a good sister
and show you what a
professional maid really is,
you creeper.
I need to grab some lead
for my mechanical pencil.
[MAIKA]
'Kay? Then I'll come with you.
Ha ha!
You really are the best!
How sweet of you to
help me with my homework!
Together we'll knock
it out by morning!
On second thought,
I've got a lot to do,
so maybe I shouldn't
come over tonight.
Adieu!
Have you no heart? Come on!
All right, I'm here.
So what's our
homework for today?
[MUSUJIME] Someday, I'm
getting out of here for good.
And I'll beat everyone
at this game that has
no way to be won.
[phone buzzes]
[KOMOE]
Hello? Hello, Musujime?
Don't forget today is the
day you're going to learn
how to make stir-fry vegetables!
I'll be here waiting for you
with an empty tummy
and visions of
stir-fried deliciousness!
I can hardly wait!
I hate to do this to you.
But something urgent came up and
we're gonna need to reschedule.
No, please! Not today, too!
That breaks my heart!
What am I supposed to do
with all these vegetables
--I just bought?
--Enjoy them, I guess?
I heard vegetarians
live longer anyway.
I seem to remember
this RV having a kitchen?
Or am I just imagining things?
[XOCHITL] I see you're
still using that face.
You must really love it,
don't you, Etzali?
[UNABARA] And you're still
as cranky as ever,
aren't you, Xochitl?
Where's the original grimoire?
I hope you thought to
put it somewhere safe.
[UNABARA]
It's right here.
So can you tell me
what happened?
Basically, I screwed up.
Then in order to make it right,
I had my own body meddled with.
No one tried to stop
you from doing it?
Tochtli?
You two were friends,
weren't you?
I don't know how to answer that.
I'm pretty sure whatever friends
you happen to be thinking of
are people with faces
I don't recognize
and names I don't know.
Don't try to tell me I'm wrong.
Whatever your reasons,
you switched camps
from Azteca to Academy City
and then took me down.
Or did you forget...
Big brother?
Damn it, Unabara!
You've got some serious
explaining to do, young man!
Quick, get back! He's probably
from the organization!
[UNABARA]
No.
Unfortunately,
this perv is on my side.
Are you really telling me
that you can lose your mind
over a Level Five
middle-school girl here
when you've got a little
sister waiting for you
back home, you freak?
What's this about
a middle school girl?
[UNABARA] I have no idea.
What's going on with you?
Be honest with me, Etzali.
Is that the real reason you
betrayed the organization?
Would you calm down, please?
Look, it's not what you think.
It's more of a
mentoring relationship
than actual siblings.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
You mean you're not related?
Well, that's fantastic,
isn't it?
Having your head
involuntarily turn
in the direction of
someone much younger
is a battle everyone must face.
That's disturbing.
What's wrong with you people?
Am I the only one in
GROUP who's not a lolicon?
Let me get this straight--
I'm being called a
lolicon by someone
who's clearly a shotacon?
Looks like it.
So true.
What have I ever done
that justifies you
calling me a shotacon? Jerks!
[UNABARA] All right, so...
What kind of job is this
that requires all of GROUP
to be called in?
Oh, just your
run-of-the-mill request.
We're supposed to find an
outfit called "Spark Signal,"
who're barricaded up
with some hostages,
and kill them all.
[TAKITSUBO]
Looks like I'm okay.
They said I might
be discharged soon.
Really?
You aren't able to
use ability crystals.
That sucks.
But at least we know
it wasn't too serious.
[KINUHATA] Still, I'm
surprised you brought her
an ultra-flower arrangement.
I thought for sure it'd
be an ultra-bunny suit.
You're on that again? Come on.
[KINUHATA]
Ta-da!
And now for our star attraction.
Ultra-Bunny Rikou!
I didn't realize you were
that ultra-hot for bunny girls.
[HAMAZURA]
I'm not!
The air's kinda dry
in here, and, uh...
You'll be okay;
we're in a hospital.
A nurse should be
coming by soon.
They know how to fix nosebleeds.
[HAMAZURA]
Thank you.
You're the only one
who cares about me!
[TAKITSUBO]
Don't worry, Hamazura.
The doctors here also offer
care for mental disorders.
Takitsubo should
be discharged soon.
Do you know what your
ultra-plans will be after that?
No, not yet.
Don't forget that ITEM
has been ultra-disbanded.
I'm waiting for a new team
to be ultra-organized.
There's ultra-no benefit
to pairing with Takitsubo
since she can't fight,
and there's ultra-no need
for you to work
with them either.
Yeah, I have no idea what
I'm going to do right now.
But Takitsubo needs to
get back into the world,
and I'm going to help her.
I hear what you're
saying, Hamazura.
You're ultra-devoting
all your time and energy
to figuring out how to get
Takitsubo into a bunny suit,
aren't you?
[HAMAZURA]
Why won't you drop that?
Is that really
who you think I am?
Ugh! Please stop ultra-looking
at me with that disgustingly
lewd stare you have
when you're imagining
girls in bunny suits!
Oh, please, you really
think I'm imagining you
in a bunny suit?
You couldn't pull off
wearing one if you tried!
Let me be ultra-blunt with
you right now, Hamazura.
I happen to have an
ultra-superior figure.
Mine's better as
a middle-schooler
than Takitsubo's is
as a high-schooler!
You're wrong about that!
I know for a fact that
Takitsubo's a knockout
whenever she gets undressed!
I also know that if
you got undressed
it would be a complete snore.
Do you want
me to ultra-kill you?
Because it sounds like
you've got a death wish!
[HAMAZURA gasps]
That was an ultra-close call!
I can't believe I was so
close to ultra-showing you
today's goodies.
How embarrassing.
[HAMAZURA]
Gross!
That might be one of
the top five worst things
I've ever had the
misfortune of hearing.
As if whatever
you've got under there
would fall under the
category of "goodies."
Check out the
ultra-skirt-flirt! Woo!
[HAMAZURA] Uh, I, uh...
I don't see anything!
[KINUHATA]
And some more skirt-flirt!
[HAMAZURA] I can't. I don't.
I can't see anything! I mean...
You'll never get to see, though.
That's why it's a skirt-flirt!
[HAMAZURA yells]
Takitsubo!
I need you to give me strength!
[HAMAZURA]
No fair!
[KINUHATA]
I'm ultra-going to kill you!
[HAMAZURA]
You show no mercy!
You are the devil!
[SPARK SIGNAL 15A] By placing
this giant particle accelerator
in a state where
it could explode,
we can keep the governing
board's over-the-top behavior
in check.
[SPARK SIGNAL 15B]
That's brilliant.
And when we're this
deep underground,
nobody will ever
be able to touch us.
[SPARK SIGNAL 15A]
It's go time.
[BOY VICTIM 15A grunts]
[SPARK SIGNAL 15A]
Show the boy a little mercy.
Blindfold him, at least.
Do you really think
this dumb plan of yours
is going to work?
[SPARK SIGNAL 15A]
Huh?
[BOY VICTIM 15A] There's
no way any of you bad guys
will be able to
get away with this!
There's a hero out there!
And I believe with all my heart
that he's coming here
soon to punish all of you!
He's going to save us!
I know there's someone
out there who will save us!
[SPARK SIGNAL 15A]
Is that so?
Let's say there is a hero.
He'll never be able to
make it a hundred meters
underground in time.
[BOY VICTIM 15A]
I still believe.
[SPARK SIGNAL 15B]
How did you get here?
[ACCELERATOR]
I'll give you a hint:
look up Move Point
sometime, you scumbag.
[SPARK SIGNALS grunting]
[BOY VICTIM 15A]
Are you the hero?
[ACCELERATOR] I'm the villain.
A punk-ass villain.
Excellent work.
That was indeed
quite the exploit.
Oh, please, it's not
like it was that difficult.
The thing that bothers
me about this
is what those damn
terrorists were demanding
from the higher-ups.
I can't believe they would
let slip the substance
of their demands!
"DRAGON."
"Disclose all information you
have concerning DRAGON at once."
That's the only demand I
heard those terrorists make.
I'm thinking the higher-ups
gave us a huge snow job,
and we walked right
into it and killed
the only possible lead we had.
Good to see you,
Stephanie Gorgeouspalace.
I was hoping you could tell me
how Chimitsu Sunazara is doing?
[STEPHANIE] He seems
to be recovering nicely.
He hasn't regained
consciousness just yet.
But his life isn't
in any danger.
Thanks to you.
[THOMAS]
Oh, that's not true.
I just feel so guilty about it.
[STEPHANIE] So, who is the
target you want taken out?
That would be
Academy City's number-one,
called Accelerator.
Think you can handle it?
[STEPHANIE]
If that is your wish.
I don't want you to
give any consideration
to whomever might be
hurt in the process
of shooting your target.
In fact, I wouldn't mind
if you took Saiai Kinuhata
and the other former ITEM
members who did this to him,
and perhaps filled
them all full of lead
while you were at it.
I think I get it.
What about the man who put a
transmitter inside his body?
If I'm taking out those
who've wronged Sunazara,
then should I add him
to the list as well?
Now, hold on!
I think this belongs to you.
[THOMAS grunts]
All you had to do was
turn over Sunazara nicely,
and I would have been
quite content to be used
as your pawn.
If you would have
just cooperated with me
like a rational person,
you could've had
your revenge against Sunazara.
This is such a waste.
Oh. I knew I forgot
to mention something.
The object of my revenge
is more than just one guy.
It's actually all
of Academy City.
[THOMAS groans]
[HAMAZURA]
Huh? What do you mean "job?"
I thought we were about
to pick up Takitsubo
from the hospital?
[KINUHATA] They're finally
organizing the new team,
so we ultra-need to get
together and ultra-kill
the remaining members
of a terrorist group.
What kind of stupid game
are they playing at now?
Takitsubo is waiting for us!
Fine. The private room
in School District Three?
[SHIOKISHI]
That bothers you, then?
If you want to be free of
unexpected misfortune,
you must never
let your guard down.
Which is why we
don't meet in person.
You're probably hiding
in what's basically
a nuclear fallout shelter.
[SHIOKISHI] For those who have
powers like the one Musujime
possesses, the thickness
of walls is no obstacle.
Mr. Shiokishi,
help me understand
why a member of
the governing board
would go out of his way
to contact us directly.
[SHIOKISHI] I want you to take
down the rest of Spark Signal--
the terrorists from earlier.
If I said the name "DRAGON,"
would that mean anything to you?
[SHIOKISHI]
Sure.
Those are the scaly
creatures with wings, right?
[ACCELERATOR]
Tch.
[SHIOKISHI] The sooner you
settle this trivial business,
the sooner you can get
back to your regular lives.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] There are
twenty members still left.
[ACCELERATOR] No doubt
killing them would be easy.
But are we just going
to submissively do
whatever the damned governing
board orders us to?
This could be our chance
to find out exactly
what DRAGON is.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] So are you saying
you want to try negotiating
with the terrorists?
Because mark my words.
If innocent civilians will be
caught in the middle of it,
I promise none of us will
be there to back you up.
I thought you were supposed
to be off fighting terrorists
with a new team,
so why are you here?
Yeah, I was.
But then I got annoyed after
five minutes and came back.
They took the survivors of the
defunct ITEM, SCHOOL, BLOCK,
and MEMBER and created
a new team with them.
Then they were like, "I know
everyone here was trying
to kill you before, but do
your best to get along!"
Oh, wow, talk about shady!
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot:
the Heart Measure lady
in the dress asked me
to ultra-give you her regards.
Really? Lucky me.
Are you sure this
is the best idea?
Blowing off an order
from the higher-ups?
I'm probably ultra-screwed.
Hamazura, would you mind
giving me a hand with something?
Huh?
All I have to do is
completely wipe out
the remaining terrorists
alone before they drag me
back into the new team!
Huh?!
Ya know, you really are
a piece of work mooching off
your friends and feeling
no remorse about it.
Did you just ultra-say
something? I don't speak Loser.
[helicopter whirring]
[HAMAZURA] Great! Looks like
we've got some major bad news
coming up behind us!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Hey!
Narrowing our avenues
of attack isn't
terribly helpful!
[crash]
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
They got away.
[ACCELERATOR] This is exactly
what you get when you cram
a busload of villains together.
And these are the
ones who shake loose?
If you want, I could blow them
up while I'm doing Spark Signal.
[HIGH SCHOOL BOY 15A]
Wait! Just a minute, please!
Stop! Don't use that drug!
[RESCUE WORKER 15A] I have to,
or she won't last until
she gets to the hospital!
[HIGH SCHOOL BOY 15A]
She's our teacher.
She's pregnant.
You have to save them both!
Please, sir!
Please, I'm begging you!
[ACCELERATOR]
Stand aside.
Sex, female.
Weight, two forty-four grams.
Heart rate, sixty BPM.
Stimulus response ratio,
coming up now as
five point five-two.
She needs a stimulant.
Two point five grams
of ephedrine.
Apply a topical patch
to the carotid artery
diffusing it in five times
for ten seconds,
and then take it off
for twenty more seconds.
That will save her.
Hey, wait!
What's going to happen to
the baby if they give her
that stuff you just said?
Do you think I did all those
calculations for no reason?
[HIGH SCHOOL BOY 15A]
Hold on, please wait!
Thank you, man.
She'll be all right
because of you.
[ACCELERATOR]
Get lost, already.
I promise I'll never forget
what you did tonight
for as long as I live.
Someday, I hope to be
able to return the favor.
You're an--
Get lost.
A six-winger.
'Kay, what does it want with us?
Hey! Did you know
they'd react like this
when you went and
disobeyed their orders?
It does seem like ultra-overkill
just for a single person, huh?
Crap! They're shooting at us!
Fun fact--the missiles
from the six-wingers
all use infrared sensors.
That flare just ultra-screwed
up their aim.
Awesome!
You need to steer
ultra-straight!
Don't turn the wheel!
I'm trying to make
it more difficult
for them to shoot us!
What the hell are you doing?
[gunshot]
Keep your eyes ultra-on the road
and your foot on the gas!
Okay, but I saw your panties!
Be careful!
There's no way you
can shoot through
a military helicopter's armor!
What makes you
think I'm trying to shoot
through the armor?
I ultra-did it with
clay-based bullets.
I figured they would
ultra-shatter
and that would cause the
fragments to enter the intakes.
Nice panties!
Damn it! Kinuhata, use
your Offense Armor!
[KINUHATA]
Hold on!
[HAMAZURA]
What am I doing?
I need to get Kinuhata
back and go see Takitsubo.
[phone buzzing]
[HEART MEASURE]
It's been too long.
If I said this is Heart Measure,
formerly of SCHOOL,
would you remember who I am?
How the hell do you
know my phone number?
[HEART MEASURE]
Never mind that.
Is Saiai Kinuhata with you?
[HAMAZURA] So, you're the
ones behind all of this!
[HEART MEASURE]
If you hear from her,
will you pass on
a message for me?
You know those terrorists she
said she'd deal with by herself?
They've just seized a private
room in School District Three.
Wait, School District Three?
Did I hear you right?
[KAMIJO] Even if I have
to become the villain.
Even if I have to get
down on my hands and knees.
Even if someone
has to be sacrificed.
I will protect her.
No matter what.
Next time, "The Governing
Board."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.