[OPERATOR 14A] We've broken
through the designated point!
Target within firing range!
[OPERATOR 12A] Large scale flash
shelling will now commence!
All witches, withdraw
from the line of fire!
I repeat, withdraw
[SMARTVERY]
Here it comes!
[OPERATOR 14A]
Targeting Buckingham Palace!
Commencing shelling!
[KAMIJO gasps]
Man, that is quite
the bombardment,
but I'm concerned
about the area around it.
The palace is surrounded
by a large park,
so I don't think stray shots
should be a major problem.
I'm more concerned
about whether an attack
that strong will even be
enough to bring down Carissa.
I'm a level-zero esper
charging into battle
with only my fist to depend on.
Pretty reckless if you ask me.
[VILIAN]
But why?
Why would you willingly
immerse yourself
in such extreme
danger when you have
absolutely no obligation
to risk your life
for the British state?
'Cause I'm not doing this
for the British state.
Think about the people
who're caught in the middle
of this coup.
They aren't just nameless,
faceless characters
created to be targets in
some arcade shooting game.
Or I'd've gone back
to Academy City by now.
But those are people.
They're all running
for their lives in terror.
Desperately clinging to
whatever's important to them
and trying not to lose it.
What kind of monster would
abandon them right now?
I'm used to William,
but you're an entirely
different sort of mercenary
than he is, aren't you?
[KAMIJO] That's wreckage
from Curtana Original's
pandimensional fragmentation!
[ITSUWA]
Everyone, hold on tight!
[KAMIJO yells]
[KAMIJO coughs]
Damn it!
Where's Index?
Kanzaki! Itsuwa!
Where the hell are you guys?
That's enough! Stop this!
My. I have to admit,
this is an unexpected twist.
The mindless little sister
is the first to arrive.
You know, if you want to
kill me, you'll have to notch
the bolt and draw back
the string first.
There's no point
in having a weapon
if you're too afraid to use it.
Here, let me
demonstrate for you!
Stop, Carissa!
Well done!
Now that's what I call an
award-winning fine play!
Already battling the final boss.
And of course,
however many knights
there are lying in wait.
If you're looking
around for an ambush,
you won't find one.
Just me.
I used them earlier for
a little live broadcast.
So you killed them?
But they were your allies!
They fought alongside you!
And you--
[CARISSA]
That's enough!
Why do you think
they're compensated
with status and riches?
It's because of their
willingness to do
whatever it takes to
protect their country.
Being expended for
the good of their kingdom
is a knight's lifelong dream.
And now as a result,
their firm solidarity
has been reborn.
If the coup d'etat
is unsuccessful,
both they and the country
will perish in terror!
They're called Griffon Skies--
mobile attack fortresses.
Unmanned magical items.
But as such, they are second
to none in coordinated attacks,
even among the nation's
other fortresses.
--[KAMIJO grunts]
--[VILIAN gasps]
[CARISSA] They're too powerful
against human targets,
so their auto-discriminators
must have been thrown off.
Ordinarily, an attack
like that would have
sliced you in half.
Princess Carissa,
you don't want to do this.
Just die.
I'm alive?
It took longer than
I would have liked,
but I've finally managed
to repay my debt to you.
Kanzaki!
[KANZAKI]
It's not just me.
Index.
Would you mind assessing
that magic for me?
Reanalyze the spell
related to Curtana.
You mean how to
control or contain it, right?
I'll give it my best try.
[CARISSA] Aren't you the lazy
soldier who couldn't even
make it to the main battle?
And now you want to be the
central figure in the fight?
I didn't mean to imply
that I was going
to settle everything by myself.
Sorry about that.
I am joined by allies now
who all have my back!
You're saying you were
holding back against me?!
Then die!
[CARISSA, KANZAKI grunting]
[KAMIJO]
That speed!
All I have to do is
distract Carissa a little
and Kanzaki will win.
Well, aren't you a brave
one to jump in like this.
Nice try.
[KANZAKI grunts]
What do you think you're doing?
Just keep going!
You guys.
Damned if you aren't
incurring an inordinate cost!
[KANZAKI yells]
Hate to say it, but it
looks like we're gonna need
your right hand after all.
[KAMIJO] I can't promise
anything, but I'll give it
a try!
There's a delay between
when Curtana cuts through
an object and when
the wreckage appears.
You can't let it throw you off.
Even if you can cancel
out the actual slice
with your right hand,
there's a real possibility
it won't have any effect
against the wreckage
that follows.
[KAMIJO] So we get close
to her after she slashes,
but before the wreckage
material appears.
[CARISSA grunts]
[TATEMIYA, ITSUWA yell]
[VILIAN gasps]
[CARISSA] At least learn
to use some decent magic!
Or is this the best the
Princess of Virtue can manage?
I can't imagine anything
more humiliating.
Save it.
I refuse to grovel to you
or anyone else ever again!
I've made a decision
for the sake of those
who are risking their
lives to save me.
I'm taking a stand as
our nation's princess!
Sod off!
[KAMIJO grunts]
[CARISSA]
What the--?
A blast from Coven Compass?
Is this a coordinated attack?
That's quite a cheeky trick!
This is the pinnacle
of relying on others...
Dear Sister!
[CARISSA]
That trajectory won't work.
[INDEX]
B-A-O.
C-D.
No way.
She survived that hit?
And with just a few scratches?
Actually, I was
hoping to drum up
a greater sense of
danger to bait my mother
and only use this once
she came a bit closer.
Calling the destroyer,
Wimbledon, on patrol at Dover.
Prepare to launch a bunker
cluster cruise missile.
Your target: Buckingham Palace!
[KAMIJO]
A bunker cluster?
[CARISSA]
You ever seen one of those?
They can destroy everything
within a three-kilometer radius.
[KANZAKI]
We won't let that happen.
We'll place a defensive barrier
in the air to intercept it.
Ha! You're assuming
you'll be able to race
against a Mach Five
cruise missile?
[KANZAKI yells]
[CARISSA] So vulnerable,
just as I anticipated!
Kanzaki!
[RIMÉA]
My goodness.
The sorcerers of this nation
should have known better.
Underestimating the
head of state as she's
wielding Curtana Original
is quite an unfortunate mistake.
[VOICE 14A] Pardon me, miss,
but you were correct.
It's a tomb, all right.
Fit for the king of
an entire civilization.
I'll send you the material.
[RIMÉA]
Indeed.
Turns out there's
a rational explanation
as to why she hasn't
killed any of them.
I understand now why you're
rushing through life,
my sister, and I know
very well what you're after.
Hello? Do you read me?
Listen up. This is
First Princess Riméa.
As you know, Second Princess
Carissa has spun wildly
out of control.
But her actions have been
entirely for the sake
of Great Britain.
[RIMÉA] We have been under
pressure from the forces
of France, the Roman Orthodoxy,
and the Russian Church.
They have all used
the EU as their pawns
and violated our
national dignity.
Amidst such humiliation,
Carissa made the decision to
wield Curtana Original herself
in hopes that we would overcome
these external pressures.
However, she also
simultaneously resolved
to lock away such a
doomsday weapon forevermore,
so that it would
never be misused again.
Once the fighting was over,
she planned to take the
destroyed Curtana Original
and shards of Curtana Second
to a hole in the ground
destined to be her grave
and spend the rest of her life
there waiting to die.
Second Princess to
Destroyer Wimbledon.
Prepare to fire.
Launch another cluster.
[RIMÉA] To protect those
who might otherwise fight
alongside her,
she is acting as a tyrant
to justify a solo battle.
She is using the weapon
to wipe out all enemies
of our nation--
both foreign and domestic.
If there are any listening
who would take pity
on my sister--
some knight, perhaps,
who would like to
save this young woman--
Would you now please take
up your sword once again?
No matter what, I can't give up.
[laughing]
Is that a fact?
Well, the second
cluster is almost here.
So what will you do?
What an ignorant fool!
Our military will
blow you apart!
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Zero out!
It's you!
[KNIGHT LEADER] Once this coup
d'état is over, you're welcome
to take my head for my actions.
But first, we have to
ensure there's a future
where that can happen.
I'm requesting that the
members of this royal family
start working together
so that we may
properly confront France
and the Roman Orthodoxy.
Forgive me.
For leaving the
fate of my country
and the fate of the
princess in your hands.
It's fine.
Let's just work together
and end this thing.
How interesting.
It seems my sister
manipulated you
with her cunning performance.
[KNIGHT LEADER] If you're
wondering what motivated me
to save you, then yes,
that was a part of it.
That's unfortunate.
I suppose I'll just
have to use all of
the bunker clusters, then.
[KNIGHT LEADER] My Thororm spell
can't stand against Curtana.
It's not that strong,
but it's more than capable
of zeroing out the
attack of your remaining
bunker clusters.
You'd only be wasting them.
I've factored
that in, of course.
The Wimbledon has
twenty-four missiles,
the King Henry the
Seventh has twenty-six,
and the Sherwood has fifteen.
If I hide one of those
behind an illusion,
then your spell
would become useless
since you wouldn't be
able to identify a target.
Second Princess to all
destroyers who are on standby.
This is an order to launch
all of your cruise missiles!
Huh? An antenna?
[ACQUA] It might be difficult to
issue an order to the military.
I see.
You would dare to
interfere with my plans?
[KAMIJO]
Acqua!
I'm sorry if I'm late;
science isn't my forte.
I'm afraid destroying
all the military antennae
in the area took a bit
longer than I expected it to.
Who would have imagined that
one day the time would come
where you and I would be forced
to work together again?
It'll be fine as long as
you don't slow me down.
Right. Come, then.
Let's put our
skills to the test.
Show me what you've learned
over the past ten years!
I'll cut off your head!
[KANZAKI] Don't think I'm gonna
let you two have all the fun.
[KANZAKI]
Single Flash!
[CARISSA grunts]
--[KANZAKI grunts]
--[ACQUA grunts]
No way.
[CARISSA grunts]
[CARISSA yells]
[CARISSA] It looks like
you've finally beaten me
at this game of hot potato.
Taking on three of you
saint-level monsters
is too much trouble.
Your mistake is
thinking "special people"
are the only ones who
can accomplish anything.
The reason we can
harness such strength
is because there are
others here who support us.
Yes, perhaps.
But I wager you never
imagined that strength
might also be your weakness.
[CARISSA grunts]
[KANZAKI grunting]
[laughing]
The greater your numbers are,
the more opportunities I'll be
able to find to rip you apart!
Whether there's a thousand
or ten thousand of you,
it won't stop me!
[CARISSA] Well, if it
isn't my dear mother.
The cause of all the commotion.
[ELIZARD] If you're going
to do whatever you please,
you should at least come
up with a better plan than mine.
Too bad. Your idea is
turning out rather terribly,
so I'm here to stop you.
Nonsense.
You only say that because
you want the throne.
Oh, no, not at all.
I'm simply appalled
at how small you're thinking.
Dearest daughter, if you truly
wish to change this nation...
You old fool.
What are you saying?
Try revolution.
Among all the state-level
Royal Household magic,
there's still one little trick
you haven't considered yet.
Now, Union Jack, I command you!
Take the tremendous
power of the British Empire,
made up of the four cultures
from which it is comprised.
Release and redistribute
it equally among
all of the British people
that they may rise up
and fight with us!
[CARISSA gasps]
The power infused
in Curtana Original...
This is Queen Regnant Elizard,
and I have a message for
the people of this country.
Many of you have
come to harm since
this coup d'état first
started without knowing why.
However, you now have the
ability to fight back!
If only for tonight,
you all have the opportunity
to become heroes.
As such, I implore you to choose
which side of history
you wish to fight for.
Weigh everything
within your own minds.
And whatever justice,
courage and nerve remains,
I ask you to heed it!
This is the opportunity for
our nation's new champions
to emerge!
All of us?
We're champions?
She's asking us to fight?
To be heroes?
[CITIZENS]
Yeah!
Right! To Buckingham!
[CITIZENS chattering]
[TSUSHIMA]
You have to get up, Itsuwa.
What the--?
It's you... Curtana?
Look around.
[TSUSHIMA]
This was the Queen's ace.
You can feel it, too, right?
This is the power
that's been shared among
all the nation's people.
Come on. It's our turn.
It's going to take
far more than that
to turn aside Curtana Original.
You're in a ninety-million
to one tug-of-war match.
Should you lose your
concentration for even a moment,
all the sword's power
will be pared away.
[KAMIJO]
This is awesome.
There are so many main
players around that myself,
Index, Kanzaki and Acqua
are just blending
into the background.
What's the deal
with this country?
It's like everyone
in it is a key figure.
She must have known this.
That's why she set
herself aside for her nation.
Okay, then.
I'm going to save the princess.
I won't let her
sacrifice herself!
[INDEX]
C-T-T-O-C-U. S-A-A-R-T-S-T.
[CARISSA grunts]
[KAMIJO]
Acqua!
[ACQUA yells]
[KAMIJO yells]
It's over. Right?
[CITIZENS cheering]
Well, that was quite the loud
show we put on last night.
It may be presumptuous
of me to say this, but...
It might have been too loud.
Was it?
I actually think our citizens
will try to measure
last night's events to no avail.
And ultimately,
I'm sure everyone
will interpret them
in their own way.
That's a possibility,
but what will we do
if they interpret last
night's events as magic?
If that happens,
we'll just have to admit it.
After all, it's not as if
there is a law stating
that magic can't be out
in the public eye, is there?
Incidentally, where did that
rather remarkable young man
run off to?
[FIAMMA laughs]
This is incredible.
A more delightful sight
than I had imagined.
Who's there?
What do you want?
If I told you that I was
Fiamma of the Right,
would you recognize the name?
I'm grateful.
It was well worth it to harass
France via the Roman Orthodoxy
in order to apply all
that stress to Britain.
And thanks to that, I got my
hands on what I was after.
What was so important
to steal that you'd go
and start an actual war?
[FIAMMA]
Perhaps no one has told you.
Or you just haven't
realized it yet,
but you are no longer needed.
Goodbye, Princess.
[laughs]
Well, if it isn't the
extraordinary right hand
I've been after!
Who's this jerk?
His name is Fiamma.
And he's the de facto leader
of the Right Seat of God.
On second thought,
I think we're done here.
I can't risk destroying
the magical item
that I've worked so hard for.
Hold on. What do you mean?
It's incredible. Want to see?
[KAMIJO]
Index?
[INDEX]
Yes. I am the magical library.
I am affiliated
with Necessarius,
0th Parish of the
English Puritan Church.
My formal name is Inde--
Index, no!
Oops, looks like
she might be broken.
Bastard! Tell me
what you did to her!
[FIAMMA]
Who knows?
But if you want to find out,
you can ask the people
responsible for creating her.
Excuse me.
I need to pop off
to Russia for a bit.
To salvage the material
needed to bring down an angel.
I'll leave you in charge
of Librorum Prohibitorum
and that fantastic
right hand of yours.
[STIYL] The stolen item
was a safety device.
One that allows her
to live a normal life,
even after memorizing
the 103,000 grimoires.
[ELIZARD]
We mucked this up.
But we'll look after her.
It's the least we can do.
Unless we can defeat Fiamma,
we'll never be able
to guarantee her safety.
Russia, huh? Stiyl.
Sorry, but I have to
leave Index in your care.
Fiamma needs to be stopped.
And I'm going to do
it with this fist.
[KAMIJO]
A moment of peace?
There's no such thing.
All that's left
are empty casings,
sad cries, and the
smell of gunpowder.
More darkness flies into motion.
Next time, "Spark Signal."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.