[PRIEST 20A] Wait. Your
Holiness, what are you doing?
[ROMAN POPE]
I must hurry.
The citizens are
overwhelmed with anxiety.
They're gathering in groups
to march on the Vatican.
Yes, I'm aware.
You need not say anything more.
[VASILISSA]
Hello there, my dandy gentleman!
Can I assume you are still
living life as the Pope of Rome?
[ROMAN POPE]
Is that you, Vasilissa?
The cardinals are about to
convene a papal conclave.
They must have decided
that my authority
is no longer what they need.
If we want to put
a stop to this war,
it will take much more
than just my words.
[VASILISSA] Nonetheless,
you have stood forward.
[explosion]
[VASILISSA]
I'm sorry about that.
I'm in the middle of bringing
the dissenters to tears.
They were trying to sell out
our beloved Sasha, after all.
[ROMAN POPE]
You must go easy on them.
They are still our brethren.
[VASILISSA]
I knew you would say that.
So enlighten me.
How are you planning to bring a
war of this magnitude to an end?
[ROMAN POPE]
I will do what must be done.
But not as the pope who leads a
flock of two billion followers.
I will act as my conscience
tells me to as a man.
And as an adherent
of the Roman Orthodoxy.
I made a promise to that
mercenary, and I will honor it.
The Lord always has a plan.
It appears His plan
for me involves enduring
even more trials.
[AIWASS]
So then, what now?
A being very much like
yourself has been identified
within Russia's borders.
She is the Archangel,
"Power of God," Misha Kruezhev.
Once the encroachment
begins, a great tragedy
will befall everyone
in that area.
[KAZAKIRI] And when that
happens, what will you do?
[AIWASS]
Nothing.
I only undertake that
which interests me.
I don't mind going.
However...
I do have one condition.
I don't want you to take
action against my friends.
[AIWASS] As long as they
arouse no interest in me,
that should be easy.
If you do hurt them,
you will have made
an enemy out of me,
and that could result
in massive destruction.
[AIWASS]
Heh.
How naive you are
to threaten me.
You never know.
You might have stimulated my
interest just by saying that.
[RUSSIAN PILOT 21A]
What was that?
An angel?
Amazing. Even way out here
in the middle of nowhere,
we can still get this stuff.
[LESSAR] Yeah, and they
all use the same recipes
so you know what to expect
even when you travel.
We've been blending in
pretty well with the rest
of the human smugglers.
But I think this is probably
as far as we're getting by car.
We still need to
get to that base,
but whattaya say we
take a different route?
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh.
Are there really this
many people all fleeing
to the same place?
To the Elizalina Alliance?
The opposite might be true, too.
I don't know anyone who
would want to be a citizen
of a vanquished nation.
We should do our best
to put a stop to this war
--as soon as we can.
--[KAMIJO] Huh?
I mean, Fiamma is the
one pulling the strings
behind the scenes, isn't he?
So all we have to do now
is kick that bastard's ass
and the war will come to an end,
and peace will finally
be restored to the world!
You're right.
Let's show Fiamma what's what,
and then we'll rescue Index.
Great, so now that
we've decided on a plan,
we can get back to this
important eating session!
[LESSAR]
Now's my chance!
I'll pay for that with my body!
Okay, get back.
I'm not comfortable with
the random lip licking
and the twinkling stars
floating in your eyes.
[HAMAZURA]
What is this?
It was the privateer base.
It's wiped out.
Is he of one of those
Academy City esper folks
you were telling me about?
That guy?
No, he isn't.
It's been handled.
That should be it for now.
I'm sorry to have to ask again,
but who exactly are you, anyway?
Acqua of the Rear.
I'm a has-been
mercenary miscreant.
There's something coming.
[HAMAZURA]
Academy City forces.
Interesting.
Looks like they're here
to occupy this territory.
What now? Drive them off?
Not yet.
If all they're doing is
defending the village,
we're better off
leaving them to it.
I'm not sure exactly
who you're supposed to be,
but you can't keep shoring
up the defenses in one spot
forever, right?
Okay, then.
It's better to let
Academy City's forces
establish themselves here.
The place will be occupied
for the time being,
but with these guys,
it will be protected
for several months.
Hold on, Hamazura,
didn't you tell me you
were trying to run away
from Academy City
for some reason?
That doesn't matter.
We still have to protect
the village, right?
Okay, it's time for us
to get moving.
Oh, wait, one last thing.
[ACQUA]
Yeah?
I owe you.
If you hadn't shown up here,
the villagers and myself
and the best girl
I've ever known--
we wouldn't have survived.
I'm gonna make it
up to you someday.
[ACCELERATOR] It looks like
some sort of instruction manual.
Fascinating.
[ACCELERATOR]
You understand it?
No, not at all.
It just looks like a list
of what appears to be
magical conversion provisions.
To the best of my knowledge,
those are instructions on how
to make a Roman Orthodox spell
work in the
Russian Church style.
[ACCELERATOR]
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I'm not like Madam Elizalina--
I don't know much
about magical things.
[ACCELERATOR]
Magic?
What the hell is
he talking about?
Does this mean there's
something that exists
that I can't understand?
If so, it could end up
being the answer I need.
Who is this Elizalina person?
Let's see.
She's either a sorceress
or a magician.
I don't care.
It doesn't really matter
to me what she is or isn't.
Do you think she'd be able
to decipher this parchment?
If she can speak.
As of right now, she's lying
in bed at a field hospital.
I don't plan on
staying here long,
and I won't be
doing any killing.
Do you know when
Sleeping Beauty will be up?
[SOLDIER 21A]
If all goes smoothly,
I'd say one to three hours.
That's good enough.
[SOLDIER 21B grunts]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[ACCELERATOR]
They're spies.
If I'm gonna leave the kid here,
it's my responsibility
to arrange a nice,
clean environment
where she can feel safe.
The place where you guys
stand isn't the only hell
that exists.
I wish I could show
you some real darkness
to compare with your drama.
[HAMAZURA]
Pathetic, isn't it?
I know. But bailing on them
halfway turned out to be
the best option for both of us.
Don't feel bad about it.
I'm not upset with you.
All you've done this whole
time is fight to keep me safe.
So no, I don't find
that pathetic at all.
[HAMAZURA]
What's this?
He says it goes to the car.
It's parked just up ahead.
Oh, no, I can't.
If I take this,
it would be evidence
that you helped us escape.
Actually, he says
you can start the engine
without using the key at all.
Try it.
Well, if you insist.
[TAKITSUBO]
Hamazura, they're coming!
It's 500 meters to the border!
We... We made it.
[metallic footsteps]
[HAMAZURA]
Seriously?
Is this the end?
[HAMAZURA]
Accelerator?
I'm right in the middle
of hunting down spies.
Do you really think I
have time to deal with
your stupid drama?
But tell me everything.
I want to hear it all.
[ELIZALINA]
This is a tough one.
I'll do what I can, of course,
but they both need
restorative magic,
and to be honest,
that takes a lot out of me.
Really? I see.
Here's what I can offer you.
I can probably handle
the girl in the track suit.
But the little one here
will be more difficult.
That's all.
[HAMAZURA]
Huh? What do you mean?
They're different.
There are two distinctive
toxins at work.
In the little one,
toxins are continuously
being injected on
a permanent basis.
So even if I removed them now,
they would be
replenished in no time.
But if I removed
them from the other,
she should have a
more lasting response.
Wait, so then you're saying
she's going to get better?
Really? You're gonna be okay!
Hamazura, I can't breathe.
I'm sorry. I'm just so happy.
[ACCELERATOR] I'm neither
surprised, rattled, nor angry.
I could stomp my feet
on the ground and scream
at the top of my lungs,
but that won't change
the outcome of this
crappy situation.
Regardless, there's not a
whole lot of time left, so...
I just have to do
what must be done.
I'm fine with whatever sort of
treatment you cook up for them.
But first,
I need you to answer
an important question.
Do you know what this
is and how to read it?
That's not something
I could answer right away.
I'd need some more
time to study it.
Do you want to leave it with me?
[ACCELERATOR]
Nope.
At least I know you can
decipher it eventually.
Anyway, I'll let you get
back to treating them.
I'm not wasting
anymore time here.
I'm taking off.
I'll see you later.
Do you have any clues?
[ACCELERATOR]
If I don't, I'll find some.
What happened to all
the spies I flushed out?
[SOLDIER 21A]
They're being interrogated,
but it's not going very well.
[ACCELERATOR]
You don't say.
Want me to take you there?
[ACCELERATOR]
Nah,
I'm gonna hunt down a more
reliable source of information.
[door opens]
Is there something
I can help you with?
Yeah, cooperate.
With what? And how? And why?
I was able to find and
recover a number of bugs.
They're yielding a
bunch of bits and pieces
from the small timers.
What I need you to do is sort
through all that information.
On what grounds does Misaka
have to cooperate with you?
[ACCELERATOR sighs] There are
some punks in Academy City.
And they're planning to
use the Misaka Network
to do something shady.
Listen.
They were replacing a network
that was causing them trouble,
and you started coming
after me and the kid
in the middle of that repair.
But you need to know
that your system
is gonna wind up
the same way--
at a dead end.
And that's just how people
who applaud the killing
of twenty thousand puppets
feel it should be done.
That's their vision
for the world.
I mean, you know it
wasn't created to be used
for any respectable
purpose, right?
So Misaka must work with you?
She should just
give in and join forces
with the most malicious
partner that ever existed?
Okay, fine.
Maybe it's time to negotiate.
Let's talk about the
Dark May Project.
You mean...
[ACCELERATOR] It was the project
that attempted to enhance
other espers' Personal
Realities by applying
the method I use to
control my ability.
For you to become an
irreplaceable resource,
you had to obtain a capacity
that the other Sisters
didn't have.
Intrigued?
The question now, of course,
is what are you going to do?
If you analyze
the way that I fight,
you could find
a way out of this.
Yes, indeed.
That truly does sound
like this Misaka's style.
[ACCELERATOR] All right, then
I'll find a lead to eliminating
the kid's symptoms.
And with any luck,
you'll stumble upon a route
other than the one where
you'll only get used and wasted.
We'll keep these goals in
mind as we fight Academy City.
And we will outwit them.
I'm glad we're on the same page.
Now, then, stop being
a baby and let's go.
[MISAKA WORST]
This Misaka must admit--
after being built solely to kill
Academy City's first-ranked,
and with everything
she's been put through,
it feels strange.
She never imagined
the day would come
when she'd have
to force a smile.
I'm sorry.
That was my mistake for
letting them manipulate me
with their bullcrap.
[laughing]
What was all that about?
When a villain makes a face
as sheepish as that one,
it makes this Misaka's
reason for existing
seem instantly less
important! [laughing]
Who are you calling a villain?
Even after I
perfected the craft,
I could never find a way to
keep the kid safe from harm!
I can't think of a single
good reason to continue
along this path.
Simply taking the side that
makes the most logical sense
isn't good enough.
You and I are both monsters.
We didn't have a choice.
We were deliberately set
to evil by Academy City.
We never opposed them.
In fact, we mastered
the ways of evil.
But it didn't matter.
We were simply chugging
right on down their rails
as planned.
But the course is changing.
It's time to make
them pay for this.
And I don't care if I
wind up doing some things
that are typically
out of character for me.
[ACCELERATOR]
Please.
You're killing me
with that dumb face!
[laughs] That stupid dead-eyed
look is hilarious!
[laughing]
I know it's Misaka's first time,
but have you ever held
someone's hand like this before?
I guess it's more
of a grip than a hold.
I have.
[MISAKA WORST]
Huh?
I've been here.
A number of times.
Each time with the
same obnoxious kid
who happens to
look a lot like you.
[KAMIJO]
Is Academy City attacking them?
Yeah, but the Russian
army is attacking as well.
Let's go.
We should take advantage
of all the chaos
and see if we can sneak
onto Fiamma's base!
Do you happen to know
why the Russian army's
coming to the base's defense?
I think it's because Fiamma
doesn't want to move.
Either he doesn't
want anyone to find out
that he's in hiding here,
or he's conducting
some kind of secret
magical operation.
Okay.
So then how do we do this?
[LESSAR] We'll steal some
of those powered suits!
I know you're overwhelmed
by my brilliance,
but you can thank me later
in bed while you gently
stroke my hair.
[KAMIJO]
Hey! Wait for me!
Damn it.
[KAMIJO]
That's strange.
When we snuck in earlier,
there were a bunch of sorcerers
from the Russian Church.
Why wouldn't some still be here?
Another thing.
Why would they act like
they're intentionally luring
Academy City in?
[FIAMMA]
Hmm...
Is it not obvious?
So you'll be motivated
to defend them
with your all-important weapon.
Not that I would
let it go that far.
I can't have you getting caught
up in the actual attack.
You might lose your
precious right arm,
and what good would
that do after all the effort
I made to get it here?
I always thought he got out
of there way too willingly.
Turns out he was just
letting me get away.
[MISAKA WORST] Those spies
are crybabies. Damn.
They didn't give us much of
a challenge, now, did they?
You guys are no fun at all!
[ACCELERATOR]
Deceptive practices are the same
as always.
The key is to remember
to deprive them
of any chance they have
to make a sound judgment.
That weepy guy talked a lot.
What'd you think?
Everything sounded contrived.
The Russian army was always
planning to take advantage
of this war to invade
the Elizalina Alliance
of Independent Nations.
They've had their sights
set on them for a while.
It seems kind of strange
that they would even send
spies at all under
the circumstances.
Those are the circumstances
that created a mission
in the first place.
They had to deliver
classified documents
to designated points
before any full-scale
aerial bombing could begin.
Once they arrived,
they would meet with someone
who was expecting this.
Meaning...
They were taking it
to somebody who knew how
to decode and use this thing.
Delicious! Misaka is
getting tingly all over
just from thinking about such
a self-serving development!
Hey, shut up!
The designated point of contact
was the Russian army's
frontline base near
the border, wasn't it?
I'm going to find
it and raid it.
That means you're free
to do whatever you want.
So then what are you
going to do with Last Order?
What would happen
if I left her with you?
Probably a lot of activity
you couldn't handle
knowing about to keep me
from getting bored.
[STIYL] There were two remote
control magical items for her.
Fiamma took the one
from the royal family.
But the puritans'
item is still here.
Also, it's obvious to me
who was in possession of it.
[LAURA chuckles]
You're trying to use
the puritans' magical item
to keep Fiamma from
misusing the knowledge
kept within the grimoires.
Your strategy is to
interrupt his magical item,
isn't that correct?
You're deliberately
confusing the programming
of her body.
[LAURA] Supposing your
delusional accusations
turn out to be true,
let's not forget I am the
head of this organization.
How far do you think
you would get dealing
with this mess on your own?
[STIYL]
If that were the case,
then I'd have no
choice but to destroy
the leader right here.
I think I understand
what you're saying.
Good thing the question
was hypothetical.
Ah, well.
I guess we'll have to wait and
see what happens, won't we?
What?
Caution. Chapter four.
Connecting. By remote user.
Connection by remote confirmed.
Automatic purge of
risk factors initiated.
Now commencing.
[NIKOLAI]
Please, don't hold back.
If you've secured Sasha
Kruezhev, then commit already!
[FIAMMA] I have finished
preparing the attack.
You will not be able to
observe the military situation.
Soon, Academy City's
trademark control
will no longer be effective.
[FIAMMA] This is about
to become a true war.
[NIKOLAI]
Proceed however you like.
I have no problem with it
as long as I achieve my goal.
[FIAMMA] The goal of
becoming the Patriarch
of the Russian Church.
You're certainly going
to great lengths for it.
[NIKOLAI]
Enough about me.
Where are you right now?
I don't see you on their base.
Your signal has
completely disappeared
from those coordinates.
[FIAMMA laughing]
Oh, you'll find out very soon.
Like it or not.
[KAMIJO gasps]
What the--? [grunts]
[LESSAR]
Oh, crap!
[FIAMMA] What I was preparing
was not some giant magical item
or facility.
It was the ability to
manipulate this space.
[PILOT 21A]
You can't be serious.
Don't you realize how much
of a risk you're taking
by doing this?
Probably not, but that's
because the risk involved
doesn't matter to me.
Between those who
are doing their best to kill
an innocent high-schooler,
and those who are
doing their best to save
that same innocent
high-schooler,
which side would
you want to be on?
Which one could you honestly
say you were proud of?
[MIKOTO]
Ugh. What am I doing?
This just isn't my style at all.
[PILOT 21A gasps, yells]
[MIKOTO]
What is that?!
No way. What's he doing?
[gasps]
You've gotta be kidding me!
Looks like the pilot is safe.
[MIKOTO grunts]
[MIKOTO]
Oh, great.
How am I supposed to get up
into the clouds from down here?
[footstep]
[MIKOTO]
Are you--?
"Misaka's serial
number is 10777,"
says Misaka, politely
answering Big Sister,
who clearly doesn't know
what to say in return.
I'm guessing by the
uniform you're with one of
Academy City's
Russian co-op outfits?
"Since the withdrawal there
has finally been completed,
the choice was made for
Misaka to have some
well-deserved private
time," says Misaka,
reporting her leisure-time mood,
while holding a
very dangerous rifle.
What do you mean
"private time?"
"Aren't you here
on private time, too?"
asks Misaka,
seeking confirmation.
[MIKOTO]
Uh... I mean...
I'm not here on business.
[KAMIJO] Wings of ice
spread across the night sky.
A giant aerial fortress.
Divine punishment meted out.
What tidings do the
angels and stars bid?
Next time, "Gabriel."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.