[LAST ORDER grunting]
[KAZAKIRI]
Look at that.
You might just
pull it off somehow.
[ACCELERATOR gasps]
[ACCELERATOR]
What the hell?
September 30th.
[gasps]
[growls]
It's happened before.
My friend Index helped her.
She was able to remove the virus
that was inside her mind.
Her method for healing involved
having the patient listen
to a very specific song.
That song's content is
within my mind as well.
Buried within.
Once you transcribe
its parameters,
I'm sure she'll be okay.
That said, if you wish to
treat her with the same song,
you must find it.
Somewhere inside her mind.
Use your understanding
of its parameters.
Are you alive?
[MISAKA WORST chuckles]
Unfortunately.
[ACCELERATOR] Then you heard
all of that craziness, right?
She listened to a song
and the virus was purged,
and the data from this same song
is buried somewhere within
Last Order's memory space.
So if you extract it and play
it, it'll help purge the virus,
is that right?
[ACCELERATOR]
Yeah.
Which means, we still have
a sliver of a chance.
It should be easy.
All you have to do is burrow
into the Sisters Network
and figure out where her
memories are backed up, right?
[MISAKA WORST chuckles]
Let's suppose Misaka is
able to locate this song.
Where exactly are
you planning to get
the additional parameters
needed to modify it
for this particular virus?
[ACCELERATOR] Academy City
and the other techniques
that exist outside of it.
If I combine the two,
there's a chance it will lead
to the perfect solution.
Takitsubo!
Answer me! Come on!
[TAKITSUBO]
Hamazura.
[gasps]
[TAKITSUBO]
Hamazura.
Long time no see!
Hamazura!
[HAMAZURA]
No way.
Mugino?
[MUGINO laughing]
[screams]
[HAMAZURA]
Ability crystals? Really?
After everything, you still
wanna make Takitsubo--
[gasps]
[MUGINO]
Takitsubo?
How foolish of you to think
I want anything to do
with your pathetic
little friend.
[MUGINO]
Tell me something.
If the fourth ranked Level Five
were to suddenly
start malfunctioning
and spinning hopelessly
out of control,
how much greater do you think
the damage she did would be?
[MUGINO laughing]
[laughing continues]
[HAMAZURA] There's no way
to get close enough to her.
Damn it.
It would be like walking
toward a blast furnace,
or the sun or something.
[MUGINO laughs]
Hamazura, I've already
given up a lot at this point.
I have paid a
considerable price--
all for this very moment.
So if you think you're
getting out of this
without giving something up,
too, you're sadly mistaken.
Hamazura.
[screams]
[yelling]
[MUGINO screaming]
--[squelching]
--[MUGINO coughs]
[HAMAZURA]
That's right.
The last time I saw her,
she was having a hard
time even standing.
[MUGINO]
Why? Why now?
Damn it.
Where the hell did my
ability crystal go?
I only needed it for
ten more seconds...
...and then it
would've all been over.
Don't you dare look
down on me, damn it!
I'm going to kill you myself--
I don't care what it takes!
It all started when you
shot me at that plant.
From that moment on,
everything has gone downhill!
[MUGINO] How was it
possible for me to become
this hideous of a monster?
Mugino.
Mugino!
[MUGINO]
What do you think you're doing?
I've had enough.
I don't get why we
all have to be out
for each other's
blood like this.
You, me, Takitsubo,
Kinuhata, even Frenda...
We used to get along
so well, didn't we?
I'm not just talking about
the way you flipped out
and killed Frenda, either.
The higher-ups in
Academy City,
if they were the ones who were
in control of all the fighting,
then they set us up to choose
violence when we felt cornered.
They wanted us to
kill each other!
If you just wanna see me
miserable, then open your eyes.
If that's what you need to stop
all this fighting, then fine--
whatever it takes!
Come on.
What do you say?
Let's stop tryin'
to kill each other.
What the hell are you even
talking about, Hamazura?
After all, you chose
Takitsubo, didn't you?
You shot me two
times to save her.
Her life was more important
to you than mine.
So why would I believe
that after all of that...
...you'd suddenly
want me to live?
Okay, you're right.
I did choose Takitsubo.
I swore on my life
that I'd protect her,
and nothing has
changed about that.
I had no choice but to abandon
you to keep my promise.
[MUGINO] You self-centered
bastard. I'm not an idiot.
I killed Frenda,
and I tried over and over
again to kill Takitsubo.
You wouldn't save me if your
own life depended on it.
I never said you'd get off easy.
Neither of us will. There are
amends to be made. By us both.
You can start by
apologizing to Kinuhata.
Show Takitsubo
you're sorry, too.
You can still shed tears
on Frenda's grave
and beg for forgiveness.
And then...
And only then, we can
become ITEM once again.
I know we can!
But in the meantime,
I'll do my best to
safeguard your life.
I'd risk my own life to get
us back to the way we were.
Don't you want ITEM back, too?
I know you do, so get up!
Come on, Mugino. Rise up on
your own just one more time!
Mugino!
You expect me to
believe a Level Zero
can somehow protect a powerful
Level Five like me?
Are you freaking kidding me?
You've got some nerve
disparaging me like that.
[engine roaring]
I guess it was always my
fate to be expendable.
That second plan is starting
to fall into place.
What will you do, Hamazura?
Like I said, I'll risk my life.
How heroic.
[STIYL] Ill effects from
the remote magical item?
Because of that pointless
intrusion into her mind,
her accuracy and speed
are coming up short.
Which means...
[INDEX] Chapter thirty-two,
verse forty-four.
Counter attack measures
are currently active.
[SASHA]
In my humble opinion,
there's a very good
possibility that Fiamma
and the Star of Bethlehem
are magically linked.
If I can attack this
star indirectly...
Dun-da-da-da-dun!
You're that lady from the
Russian church, aren't you?
Looks to me like you're
sailing up a rough creek,
so I'm here to tell you
about the payment plan.
[LESSAR]
If you look over there,
you'll see some
emergency escape pods.
I figured... with the
way Fiamma works,
he would probably ditch
the Russian sorcerers
as soon as he was
done with them.
So I thought I could
show 'em a way outta here.
[SASHA]
Question one, if I may:
What payment plan?
Well, it wouldn't be with money.
If you will make a pledge
to help Britain out
the next time they find
themselves in a tight spot,
we could call things even.
This is my first answer:
Gather everyone who wishes
to leave the front lines
and take them away at once.
I have no intention of leaving
here... until I get back at Fia.
Heh, heh, heh!
Fine! As you wish!
Wait.
Were you saying you
wanna get back at Fiamma?
My second answer, if I may:
I am not obligated
to respond to you.
[LESSAR grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
The Star of Bethlehem
is among the heavens.
With the power of Gabriel,
I've manipulated
the celestial bodies.
Each of the four
elements have returned
to their proper positions.
The arrangements
have all been made.
So now, I think it's time
I claimed your right hand.
Then we can finally declare
Project Bethlehem complete.
Oh, can we?
That's how badly you want the
Roman Orthodox Church to win?
[FIAMMA] I couldn't care less
about that organization.
Everything I've done has
been for one reason.
And that one reason is me!
[KAMIJO]
Can I cancel him out?
No!
Oh!
I see you've learned not only
how to zero out an attack,
but also to fend it off.
[FIAMMA] Is that an Academy
City optical weapon?
[gasps]
As I've demonstrated before,
my right arm optimizes its
output to match the difficulty
of whatever trial I might
currently be facing.
So optical weapons, or anything
else they may have...
...are simply a waste of time.
They're no match for me.
This is ridiculous.
On the other hand,
you should be proud.
My fist appears
to be at somewhat
of an uncharacteristic
loss in that...
...it doesn't know how
hard to hit you.
Warning. Chapter
twenty-two, verse one.
Eli Eli Lama Sabachthani
is now activating.
It does seem to have
its disadvantages
as a straightforward spell.
[yells]
[FIAMMA]
Warning.
Chapter twenty-nine,
verse thirty-three
is currently activating.
[KAMIJO groaning]
[KAMIJO]
Damn it.
He's using Index's knowledge
and combining it with his
Right Seat of God skills.
Warning, this is chapter
thirty-five at verse eighteen.
"Brimstone Rain Shall Burn
the Earth" now activating.
[FIAMMA]
How terrible.
It strayed from its
theoretical value.
I think I'd feel bad
using it on any adversary
who was dragged out
into the open like this.
So I'm an adversary now?
Enlighten me.
What can I say?
This world is twisted.
It feels like it's aging,
in the same way that humans do--
breaking down and going mad.
And that's despite God
supposedly having arranged
all the gears so that
everything turns correctly.
[FIAMMA] How did things
become this bent out of shape?
The answer is simple.
It's because a number
of these gears
have already reached
their limits.
So I'm restoring them
to their original form.
[FIAMMA]
I'm altering the mechanisms,
exchanging the gears, and
eradicating the contamination.
Bathing the world in the ways
of the church of the cross
as it was intended,
and restoring it to its
former graceful motion.
[KAMIJO] So basically,
you're going to use magic
to alter other people's minds
however you see fit,
is that right?
It's much simpler than that.
I desire only to
teach them a lesson.
Look, all I have to do is wield
my perfect arm one time
and humanity will finally see
how tragically
outmatched they are.
That's when they'll realize:
The only thing required
of them is to obey,
and right before their
eyes, I, in turn,
will save every single
person in the world.
Just wait for that instant
when the Star of Bethlehem
lights up the night sky.
That's the moment when it will
become clear to everyone,
and we can all celebrate the new
age that has already begun!
[KAMIJO] You're gonna
save the world, huh?
The only way that makes sense
is if you just haven't had time
to get out and
look at the world.
Have you seen
their smiling faces?
What are you trying
to save them from?
Interesting view.
And I'll think on it.
But not now.
We'll have to catch
up at another time,
as I've got a world to save.
[KAMIJO screaming]
[FIAMMA chuckles]
Got it.
[laughing]
Imagine Breaker may have started
as a type of purification
that was naturally instilled
within the sacred right arm,
but as it takes on my power--
one of its original components--
that unnecessary function's
role comes to an end.
My right arm will
finally be complete.
The only thing left to do
is wield the full power
that rightfully
resides within me
and I will provide
salvation for all.
People may start referring
to me as Kamijo,
the "Person Superior to God,"
but I don't care.
As long as this power can
be used to save the world,
I will succeed.
[FIAMMA]
The time has come.
I will save the world.
Hey! Be grateful!
At least you had the opportunity
to do something good
with your life!
What? No.
[FIAMMA]
I've assimilated your right arm,
so how can it be possible
for you to deflect me
without any power?
[FIAMMA]
What is he doing?
Something's happening.
But it's invisible.
[KAMIJO]
That's it.
I don't know who
you think you are
or who you're supposed to be.
It's not a mystery
worth solving to me.
I couldn't care less about
what you're trying to do.
But...
...whatever it is, drop it!
I'll handle
everything from here!
What? No.
You renounced it--willingly
gave up that much power,
and reclaimed your
Imagine Breaker from me?
[KAMIJO] I'm finally starting
to understand some of this.
Oh? Do tell.
Why did you have to construct
the Star of Bethlehem
on such a large scale?
If you, Fiamma of the Right,
really were some almighty being,
you wouldn't have had to
scrounge up different parts
from churches and cathedrals
around the world,
now would you?
Why go to so much trouble
to cause World War Three?
Your power changes to
match the difficulty level
of your opponent.
And because of that, the amount
of power you're able to use
is completely dependent on
someone else's strength.
But what could you
possibly want to achieve
that requires that much power?
Were you so desperate
that you had no choice
but to team up with other sects?
And if you're so invincible,
why would you ever need to
have people working for you?
Admit it. You were
terrified, weren't you?
Because the truth of the
matter is that you actually
don't know if you'll ever really
have enough power in you
to save the world.
The world has never
come to an end before.
And unfortunately for you,
I haven't heard anything
about it falling apart
in modern times.
Unfortunate because...
that's why you can never tell
if you have enough power
to save the world or not.
It's like my Imagine Breaker.
There's no way to
know what it can do
unless I'm surrounded by
espers and sorcerers, right?
So then... if you've never
been put in the position
to save the world,
you can't accurately claim
to have the power
that's required to do it.
And that's the real reason you
had to take things this far!
[FIAMMA]
So what if I did?
What right does someone like
you have to condemn me for it?
Or are you trying to tell me
that you've experienced
the kind of power it takes
to save the world?
Of course I have!
And yeah,
it may have been something
seemingly unimportant...
...but I have saved others.
Even when doing the
smallest of tasks,
I've witnessed the moment
when a single individual's
"world" was saved.
Someone who thinks they
can save the entire world
will only destroy it.
Our world isn't as
fragile as you think.
It doesn't need to be
saved by some bastard!
[chuckles]
[MIKOTO sighs]
Well, it looks like that's it.
Luckily, tanks are a lot
faster than I expected.
"Seeing you singlehandedly
run over them,
Misaka can't keep from
feeling inferior,"
Misaka says, as she
looks at you dejectedly.
What are you talking about?
All of you put together
could destroy me!
"You are referring, of course,
to our collective strength
while individuality is something
Misaka would desperately
like to have.
You could not possibly
understand how that feels,"
says Misaka, mumbling
bitterly under her breath.
Anyway, if I'm right,
you do have some knowledge
on how to operate the weapons
installed here, don't you?
[MISAKA 10777]
If needed,
it is possible to access
extra information
from the Misaka Network.
[MIKOTO] I'm not sure
if they were using this
for aerial combat or
transportation or what,
but there's a VTOL fighter
over there, right?
I bet we could use that.
If so, we can fly right up
to that fortress in the sky,
can't we?
[KAMIJO]
People don't just have malice,
they have benevolence, too.
They fight, pray, and stand up
for those they wish to protect.
And they don't need
any other reason.
Next time, "Wings."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.