Alert every knight hidden
throughout the land!
Be ready to move quickly!
Let the invasion commence!
Curtana Original
is now in our hands!
Those who do not wish to
see their country befouled
are invited to rise up
with me, Carissa,
as I am now your
new head of state!
This is the start
of a new United Kingdom.
We will improve whatever
we see as necessary.
And whatever we don't need
will be destroyed!
[SISTER 10B] The knights are
even coming after those of us
in Necessarius.
I need to rendezvous with the
sisters in the other fortress
so we can regroup.
[SISTER 10B]
Oh, no!
[OPERATOR 12A]
Attention!
Three through twenty and
thirty through thirty-five,
ready to fire!
Designated witches will
please accelerate in sequence
and attend to
intercepting the knights.
What do you think
about this, Smartvery?
There's no way to be
certain that our attacks
will have any effect against
those knight monsters.
Guess our only choice
is to tough it out
until Coven Compass
crosses the border.
Great. So we're decoys, then?
Knights do love to
chase after witch tail
no matter what year it is.
Right, here we go!
[KNIGHT 12A] We have
instructions to avoid
lethal force
whenever possible,
but with this many
of us in one fight,
I'm afraid there will
be no guarantees.
So you're suggesting
we surrender to spare us
from danger.
How generous of you, sir.
[KNIGHT 12A] You don't
care if your people die?
[KNIGHTS yell]
[KNIGHT 12A]
What?!
Spread out and begin
searching the area!
They couldn't have
gotten too far away.
[KNIGHTS]
Sir!
Well, well, that worked out
even better than expected.
Yes, but what do we do now?
[AGNESE]
Hmm...
[LAURA] My goodness, I had
intended to call in the List
of Prohibited Books
and have her determine
whether the First, Second,
and Third Princesses
posed a threat before
something as drastic
as this happened.
It's likely the militaristic
second princess's work.
Given the number
of knights involved.
Hmm. Very impressive, her
locating the Original like that.
As a result, Curtana Second
here is all but useless.
I might have a parent's bias,
but so far the invasion's
going splendidly.
Yes, it's been wonderful.
Perhaps her fool mother
should just stick her head
in the noose right now.
[KNIGHT 12C] Offer no
resistance, and you needn't come
to any undue harm.
Please choose wisely.
This must be quite
rough for you.
That is not the way
Carissa operates.
Her orders would've been
more along these lines:
"If she doesn't obey you,
kill her without hesitation.
Once you decide to kill her,
show no mercy."
[KNIGHT 12C gasps]
Well, then, shall we?
[INDEX] From what I can sense,
a Roman Orthodox spell
based on the lore of
the House of Loreto
was used as a destruction glyph.
[CARISSA]
Hmm.
[INDEX] The original House
of Loreto is famous
for having been visited
by King Louis IX of France.
And he was known for
his magical item theory.
It's possible someone updated
it and used it to cause
the blast in this tunnel.
[CARISSA]
Well, that is excellent news,
and not just for me,
but for you, as well.
Your analysis of the spell
and its connection to France
is definitive proof that they
were involved in the blast.
If you had denied
their complicity,
things would have gotten ugly.
I wouldn't have had any
choice but to kill you
right here, right now.
Issue the ultimatum
to France immediately.
Then mobilize the military.
Get the destroyers to Dover.
I want them ready to fire
on Versailles at any moment,
pending France's response.
Should we consider Academy City?
Ignore them.
This is our military might.
And we alone must
hold the reins to it.
To hell with this damn war.
The Puritans, Academy City,
the Orthodoxy, and
the Russian Church.
We can't win.
Whether magic or science
is victorious in this fight,
Britain will go down
for having gotten mixed up
with both sides of the battle.
If we're going to avoid that,
we can't wage a war
of just two powers.
Instead, we must make
it a three-sided war
for British independence.
Mother's way isn't
aggressive enough.
For the sake of
our nation's future,
we need to win
this war on our own,
without help from anyone.
Their interference
will only weaken us.
Well, then, that just
leaves my mother.
And my sisters, too, of course.
To secure my claim to the
usage of Curtana Original,
we'll have to kill them at once.
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Right.
Damn, those knights
are everywhere.
[LESSAR grunts]
We need to go and meet up
with Necessarius quickly.
She's fading fast.
--[blast]
--[BOTH gasp]
Are you kidding?!
[KNIGHTS yelling]
Wait, Golem Ellis?
Sherry's making a move?
[SHERRY laughing]
[ORIANA] She looks like
she's completely unhinged.
I forgot.
Of course.
A friend of hers was
killed by a knight.
Looks like we
have a distraction.
Use it to get her to
Necessarius's dorms.
I'm going to knock out those
knights while they're busy
fighting the golem and
then wait for the chance
to bring the sorceress
back to her senses.
You really think you can
handle that by yourself?
You mean, "Good luck
out there. I trust you"?
If you don't trust me,
then you can always
abandon the girl
and stay here to help.
Once you deliver her,
head to Waterloo station
and find a way to sneak
aboard the Eurostar train.
The knights will be using it to
move people and goods around.
Why would I do that?
The train will take
you to Folkstone,
where you'll find
what you're looking for.
Namely, Carissa and the
List of Prohibited Books.
Good luck. I trust you.
There, that's better.
Go, I've got things here.
[CARISSA] I was wondering
how she sensed the danger
she was in.
I see.
The servants are to
blame for her escape.
The virtuous third daughter
lives up to her reputation.
[KNIGHT LEADER] Princess
Vilian's carriage appears
to have headed toward
Canterbury by way of Dover.
That's where the English
Puritans' main cathedral
is ostensibly located.
For being the
slow-witted sister,
she made an impressively
quick getaway.
Let's go.
We don't have any time
to waste at this point.
We'll kill Vilian
with all haste,
then go after my older sister.
An aircraft.
Really?
[CARISSA]
Is it hostile?
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Likely so.
We haven't received word
of any reinforcements.
I'll bring it down.
Too late. It's here.
This mess you created
is going to take
a very long time to untangle.
But defeating the ringleader
should speed things up.
I don't have time for this.
Please, allow me
to take care of her.
Is that why you were so
determined to get me here?
Because you knew it was
going to end up like this.
My desire to see you behave
in a more ladylike fashion
was unfeigned.
Though, it seems it's
too late for that now.
[KANZAKI yelps]
[KANZAKI grunting]
I don't understand why
you're so surprised.
This kingdom was first
forged around Curtana
and our four cultures,
and that itself binds us
under unique
church-of-the-cross rules.
You see, within our realm,
the king is the archangel.
Which means the
knights are angels.
[KANZAKI grunting]
I don't care if you are a saint.
As long as we're in this land,
my power is on an
entirely different level.
[VILIAN] I'll head to
Canterbury Cathedral.
If there are any puritans
remaining when I get there,
I must ask if they'll
rescue the servants
who allowed me to escape.
--[horse neighs]
--[VILIAN gasps]
[CARISSA]
What are you waiting for?
Hide if you want, but you
might as well come out.
You're going to die either way.
Three, two, one.
[VILIAN screams]
[CARISSA] If you're counting
on Canterbury Cathedral,
don't bother.
Do you understand?
Foolish little girl.
Your carriage losing
control wasn't our doing.
You have Canterbury and
their autopilot magical item
jamming to thank for
your current situation.
The puritans have forsaken you.
You're wrong!
That can't be true!
Give up already,
you pathetic brat.
There isn't a single
soul left on your side.
Not a single one.
The saint won't
bother us anymore.
Nothing stands in our way.
Would you do one
more task for me?
Of course.
I won't use a sword, though.
An axe.
That's generally the preferred
weapon for executions.
[VILIAN gasps]
You're free to beg for
help if you would like to.
Perhaps somebody's
even listening.
I wouldn't expect anyone
to answer you, though.
[VILIAN]
There's no one.
I'm all alone.
Nobody is going to help me.
Nobody.
It's time now.
But I will make one promise
before we must say farewell.
I will take all measures I can
to ensure your head is
well-preserved after death.
It will remain as beautiful
as it was in life.
That those who see it
may honor your memory.
[VILIAN whimpers]
[KNIGHTS yelling]
[KNIGHT 12D]
He returned.
Interesting.
You're really back.
[GROUP]
William Orwell!
Have you been injured,
third princess of the realm?
What took you so long?
What took you so long,
you washed-up
mercenary scoundrel?
Where have you been?
Kill them both. Go, now.
I'll bring you their heads.
[VILIAN]
Bayard?
The location of Necessarius's
safe house has been input.
You're leaving now, Princess.
But William, what about you?
I'll catch up with you shortly.
Don't worry too
much about pursuit.
I'll do all I can to keep
them from following.
You're going to go
up against the knights
all by yourself?
And Carissa?
You intend to fight
the person who is now
effectively the state?
Just forget me.
I'll be all right.
You saved my life.
That's already more than
anyone else in the world
would have done for me.
I'm not the sort of person
people want to save.
Please cast me aside and be off.
If you go now, at least you'll--
William, what are you doing?
You may not believe
in my strength,
but don't doubt my dedication.
The reason I fight for
you remains unshaken
and always will, Princess.
No!
[VILIAN]
Idiot!
Don't you understand
that isn't what I wanted
to hear from you?
[KNIGHT LEADER] Why do
you stand here against me,
even now?
You are William Orwell,
the onetime mercenary.
And now Acqua of the Rear,
one of the Right Seat of God.
I see no possible reason
for you to risk your life
for our nation's Third Princess.
Very well.
It seems that no matter who
you are or who you're with,
It doesn't change
what you must do.
So... That truly is the way
that you see the world.
The magic item Hrunting.
[KNIGHT LEADER] Many things
have changed in the ten years
since you left.
As you can see, I'm no
longer the same man
you knocked out in Dover.
I'm ready to stake my ten years
of experience against yours.
Let's see what
you've accomplished
during your long absence!
[KAMIJO] Lessar's with
Necessarius and I made it
aboard the train.
[KAMIJO]
A patrolman?
They're checking in here?
--[FLORIS] Hey.
--[KAMIJO gasps]
You're not from around here.
And you definitely don't
look like you're working
with the knights.
Um, no...?
[KAMIJO]
Huh.
I feel like I've seen that
outfit somewhere before.
Is that the style now?
[FLORIS]
Then you can help me.
Hi, my name is Floris,
and I dabble a little bit
in a minor sorcery society.
Now don't just sit there.
Get me out of this thing.
We're almost to
the end of the line.
[KAMIJO]
A sorcery society?
Those restraints they've got
you in look really sturdy.
What exactly did you do?
Uh, well...
I don't think I did anything
that was too wrong.
This is just overkill.
Oh, and these are magical items,
so you'll never get them
off without the keys
over by the door.
[FLORIS gasps]
Uh, sorry.
Thing is, my right
hand's actually called
Imagine Breaker.
It's got this weird ability to
cancel out magical objects
and stuff.
[FLORIS]
Idiot!
Breaking the restraints
off so roughly like that
is going t--
[alarm blaring]
Wonderful!
[whines]
We're gonna hit a dead
end in about ten minutes!
No. It's too soon
to give up yet.
[FLORIS]
Wait, you're not thinking--
Desperate times and all.
Are you crazy?
I don't have a death wish.
There's a river just
ahead that should work.
Jumping's our only chance.
Let's go!
[FLORIS yelling]
Oh, man, we're
gonna die! For real!
We're gonna be fine!
The water will cushion our fall.
Yeah, except that river is
no more than a meter deep,
you jerk!
[KAMIJO]
Huh?
Whoa, watch my right ha--
[BOTH yelling]
Your wounds ache, don't they?
I can see them hurting
more with each blow.
Are you suffering
the aftereffects
of your defeat in Academy City?
Why are you talking when
you should be fighting?
Can you no longer take up
your sword and do battle
without making excuses
for your actions,
both to yourself and
to everyone else?
[KNIGHT LEADER yells]
[ACQUA yells]
It's such a pity.
If this is the great
battle of our lives,
then I would have
preferred to fight you
when you were at your best.
[ACQUA grunts]
[ACQUA]
That was not Hrunting.
Changing your attack pattern?
I'm just impressed you
realized it so quickly.
And here I was hoping
we'd be able to settle things
between us without
me having to use this.
That's not like you.
I wouldn't think
you'd hold back
against the sign
of the evil dragon.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Movement Speed!
And Weapon Weight!
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Slicing Power!
Attack Range!
That's all you have.
You have no chance of overcoming
my blade in your condition.
I'll give you a choice.
Lay down your sword
and leave the country now.
Or stay and become one with
the United Kingdom's soil.
Which would you prefer?
Before I choose,
I have a question for you.
If you support the
Second Princess
and her bloody coup d'état,
and kill the third princess,
do you truly believe it will
salvage this nation's future?
It isn't the ideal course.
However, history is
already in motion.
As such, I had no choice
but to take a side.
So I have chosen,
and I believe this path
will bring the most
benefit to my country.
I see.
Will you flee, or will you die?
Neither.
The real question is,
will I kill you,
or will I let you live?
Very well.
It appears I have
my answer, then.
So be it.
Prepare to die!
[LAURA]
How about that?
I managed to get us
out of our restraints.
Are you insane?
That wasn't "getting us
out of our restraints"--
it was just an explosion.
As long as the
outcome's the same,
who really cares
about the process?
Whatever you call it,
the carriage is a wreck now.
What are we supposed
to do about transportation?
[LAURA]
Uh... Never fear!
I have a terrific
idea about that.
[ELIZARD]
Huh?
No! Please tell me
you're not doing
what I think you're doing.
Yes!
It's the hitchhiking gambit!
Hey, driver of that
wretched-looking lorry there.
How would you fancy a
drive with this beautiful lady
and her companion?
That was rude.
Moron.
The driver clearly
made the right decision.
[horse whinnies]
All right!
London, here we come.
What are you waiting for?
What?
You really think I know
how to do something
as brutish and uncouth
as riding a horse?
[ELIZARD]
Off we go! Ha!
[LAURA] Wait, you can't
just leave me here!
Come back! I'm serious!
What do you expect
me to do? Hitchhike?
[KAMIJO]
The sword rips apart dimensions,
and engulfs Britain
in a sea of flames.
Will the sorcerers
be able to withstand
such overwhelming power?
Next time, "Curtana Original."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.