Hacking by way
of magic, are you?
[KANZAKI yells]
You really are quite
something else.
But it seems to me
your body is screaming
from all this high-speed
combat, isn't it?
[KANZAKI] The power of Gabriel
dwelt within Misha Kruezhev.
That incarnation seems
to have been incomplete.
But I'm sensing something
greater from Acqua.
Still, can a human really
possess this much power?
[KANZAKI yells]
It's been a long time since
I've had a decent workout.
However, it's about
time to finish this.
[ACQUA]
T-H-M-I-M-S-S-P!
What is this?
[ACQUA]
T-C-T-C-D-B-P-T-T.
R-O-G-B. W-I-M-A-A-T-H!
Now tell me where
to find Imagine Breaker.
Perhaps,
if I continue breaking through
all the various levels,
I may eventually run into him.
[KANZAKI]
Acqua!
[KANZAKI coughs]
You are no longer in any
shape to continue fighting me.
[KANZAKI] I won't let the
reason that boy demonstrated
or the conviction he showed
by risking his life
be trampled underfoot
by this coward.
With nothing but his talent!
[KANZAKI gasps]
[KANZAKI yelling]
[ITSUWA]
What in the world was I doing?
I feel like I was putting
in grueling effort,
but compared to
both of those saints,
I may as well have been
playing some kind of a game.
[MIKOTO]
Aw, damn it!
I don't know if the system
is glitching or what,
But now I'm stranded because
of this low-oxygen alert.
And to top it all off,
the gate is malfunctioning,
so I can't get back
to the ground level.
This sucks!
[gasps]
You're not looking so good.
Is everything okay?
Hey, is that you, Misaka?
I have to go.
Huh? Wait, hold on!
Dummy. What's going on?
What happened to you?
Don't tell me you snuck
out of the hospital.
I really have to go.
They're fighting.
Still. I have to go, too.
They're close.
I have to find them.
[MIKOTO]
Why won't you just say it?
That you need my help!
Or that you need
help from someone!
Just say that you feel
scared or anxious!
You don't even have to
be specific about why!
Misaka, what are you saying?
Listen. I know all
about it, okay?
I know that you have amnesia.
I get that you're carrying
the weight of something huge
inside of you.
But is it absolutely
necessary for you to carry it
all by yourself?
You look like you've been
through the wringer.
You even lost your memory.
So what reason could
you possibly have
to keep doing things alone?
I can fight too, you know.
I'm serious!
I can be of help to you!
So say something.
Tell me where you're going
and who it is
you're about to fight!
I want to make this easier.
I'm gonna fight too this time!
Misaka.
Whatever. Fine.
You're not listening
to me anyway.
I'll watch out for you
until you go back.
So. I guess you found
out about all that,
but you've got it wrong.
I can't remember
who I was before,
but apparently I wasn't the
kind of guy who was willing
to ask for help.
The me that I can't remember
is the one who is
driving who I am now.
He's still there.
Maybe not up here.
But here.
If I don't know,
he still understands.
He knows what I
want to accomplish
and what to do.
I'm sorry, Misaka.
But you should hurry
up and get going.
When you think about
it, nothing's changed.
Even if my gears hadn't slipped
and I hadn't lost my memories,
I'd still be doing
the same thing.
I wouldn't be able to
leave it to someone else.
That's not Toma Kamijo.
He's not shaken by whether
or not he has his memories.
[MIKOTO] There's nothing
wrong with what I said.
He has to get back to
the hospital right away.
Even though I have the
option of going with him
and assisting with the fight.
Should I?
I mean, I believe what he said,
and there's probably
some special significance
for him in standing
on his own two feet.
So if that's the case, it
wouldn't be right to stop him.
The best thing I could do
is see him off from here.
What now?
I don't feel satisfied
by that at all.
[MIKOTO]
Oh. That's why.
[KANZAKI yells]
[ACQUA] Are you finished
already, Saint of the Far East?
[KANZAKI] How can he
possibly wield such power?
Drawing forth that much
from one being
should instantly
disintegrate a person's body
both physically and magically.
Not to mention,
Acqua's power is from
the Right Seat of God.
This shouldn't be possible.
It's beyond the realm of
potential and natural talent.
There is no way
he can condense two
extraordinary aptitudes
into a single body like this.
There's more to it.
He must be using
some sort of trick.
Saintly powers and those
from the Right Seat of God
are incompatible.
What's allowing them to coexist?
So you still intend to fight!
I bet you're fuming right now.
Telling yourself not
to drag civilians
and Amakusa Church
members into a fight
between saints when our
powers are so vastly different.
But that's the nature
of the battlefield.
Differences in abilities,
the quality of weapons,
the strength of numbers.
Attacking others with
such obvious disparities
is the rule here.
If you don't like that,
then too bad!
You shouldn't have come
here in the first place!
[KANZAKI grunts]
[ACQUA] There is absolutely
no reason to make those
who have no power fight.
It shouldn't be done.
Only true soldiers should be
the ones to take up swords!
I'm sure I've never heard a
more arrogant way of thinking.
How could I have
been such an idiot?
What is the right
decision to make?
What choice will ultimately
save my friends?
What choice will finally correct
Acqua of the Rear's mistake?
What will uncover his secret?
And what choice
could I possibly make
to counteract his
overwhelming power?
Help me. Give me strength.
Yes, I need your strength!
[ITSUWA gasps]
Let's move!
It's time for us to bring
the Amakusa Church
where it needs to be!
[AMAKUSA CHURCH yells]
What's this?
You're seeking salvation
from the weak?
Is this how badly you
fear the fate of death?
Is that what it looks like?
It's true that I have
friends who were hurt
standing by my side, and I
feared it would happen again.
Because of that,
I decided to rethink my
involvement with the Amakusa.
But I was wrong.
This tragedy did not happen
because they were weaklings.
I labeled them as weak,
and I was unable to
trust in their abilities.
Somewhere inside me,
I looked down on them.
And I would never
allow them to protect me.
The real tragedy is my
arrogance in believing
that I was the one who
had to protect them.
And that's why I'm
going to overcome it.
I'll trust them to have my back.
And with all of us trusting
and supporting each other,
I will surmount this.
And the Amakusa Church will
have the revival it deserves!
[ACQUA] Your baseless hope
is simply a delusion.
What's wrong with you?
Did you truly think you could
surpass me by doing this?
[KANZAKI] Saints were born
with physical characteristics
very similar to the Son of God.
So they have a portion of
that power on loan to them.
[KANZAKI]
Be that as it may...
They cannot wield the kind
of power that you have.
You clearly have powers
above those of a simple saint.
And why is that?
The answer's obvious.
It's your Holy
Mother Veneration.
You have physical
characteristics not just similar
to the son of God, but to
the Holy Mother as well.
By stacking the attributes of
both saint and Holy Mother,
you've taken that power
that would normally
run out of control,
and found a way to
forcibly integrate it!
So what difference does
it make to you if I have?
It doesn't.
Because you have an
unfortunate weakness.
Compared to all the
other saints in the world,
you have an even greater
vulnerability to counter spells
that specifically target you!
She means Saint Breakout.
[KANZAKI]
Saint Breakout.
It forcibly collapses
the balance of traits
similar to the Son of God.
And this causes the power
to run rampant within them.
If you have both those traits
and are then hit with
a Saint Breaker spell...
He would detonate.
It makes sense.
That's why he was exclusively
using his magical abilities
defensively when
we fought earlier.
I see. So that's your play.
[KANZAKI yells]
These are all symbols
from the crucifixion
of the Son of God.
[KANZAKI] Longinus,
It's time for the final key
to his execution!
This should be good.
Fighting against the
entire Amakusa Church.
Such is a name worthy to
be engraved upon my heart
for all time.
[ACQUA]
T-H-M-I-M-S-S-P.
T-C-T-C-D-B-P-T.
T-R-O-G-B-W-I-M-A-A-T-H!
[AMAKUSA CHURCH yells]
[ACQUA yelling]
Go, now!
What the--?
Just leave him to me!
I've got this
Saint Breakout!
[ACQUA yelling]
[KNIGHT 9A]
Sir William, you're safe!
[KNIGHT 9B]
That's William Orwell for ya!
That's what you
get for tricking me
and saving the best
part for yourself.
So, is it true what I've heard--
that you're really planning
to leave England?
[ACQUA (WILLIAM)]
Yes.
[VILIAN gasps]
[KNIGHT LEADER] You're not cut
out to be a mercenary, William!
I pulled so many strings.
I had hoped to finally
welcome you in as a knight,
but you didn't care.
You just brushed it all away.
What is it you're going after?
It's not that I'm turning
it down for a better option.
Knights and mercenaries
are both important roles.
You know that.
Changing won't solve anything.
Meaning what?
We're fine as-is.
I protect from without.
Meanwhile, you safeguard
everything from within.
It's perfect.
We'll have greater
latitude this way.
I guess there's
no stopping you, then.
[ACQUA (WILLIAM)]
Oh, that reminds me.
Could you do me a favor?
An order has been
placed with a craftsman
outside of London
for an escutcheon.
Cancel it for me, would you?
[KNIGHT LEADER]
As though he could lay it aside.
As though it could
be laid aside.
Damn it.
Looks like you're
coming around!
Uh, here.
See if this helps.
Oh, no! Please don't
strain yourself!
Not after the battle
you've been through.
Uh, actually, to be honest,
I don't remember
much of anything
after I'd left the hospital.
We took down a saint!
There's not even twenty
of them in the entire world!
And you were a big part of that!
That on its own is a miracle!
Just like a shooting star.
Or like Santa Claus
tripped and all the presents
were scattered everywhere!
You know?
Sure.
So then, you're basically
saying we beat Acqua
and that you and the
Amakusa are awesome?
Oh! No!
I didn't mean it like that!
Although, I have
to admit it's true.
But it's not really
for me to say, so...
Wait. Can you tell me
what day it is today?
My attendance numbers
are still okay, right?
Please say yes!
There have been so many
incidents happening lately.
You shouldn't be getting up!
Just lay back down!
Uh, I mean, if you...
[INDEX]
Toma...!
I'm the one who was sitting
there for most of the time
and you didn't even notice.
[BOTH gasp]
We were talking!
[INDEX] You haven't even
apologized for sneaking out
of the hospital
without telling me!
Yeah. She's right!
[KAMIJO]
Huh?
How could you do that?
You shouldn't've been fighting
Acqua in your condition!
As in Acqua from
the Right Seat of God?
Why wouldn't you think
of turning to me for help
against an enemy who's
that powerful, Toma?
Uh... Well, uh...
Wait, when did Itsuwa
start taking Index's side?
Is this the Amakusa
environmental adaptation
ability at work?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Hey, there, sweetie.
While you're standing there,
the window of
opportunity is closing.
[KANZAKI gasps]
You need to find a suitable
way of thanking Kami
for all the help he gave
the Amakusa, don't you?
I intend to express
my gratitude.
--I just--
--Well?
I assume you brought your fallen
angel maid set along, right?
No! Of course I
didn't bring it here!
Really.
I couldn't do that with
others around anyway,
but especially not considering
that girl's perfect memory.
Yeah, I figured you might
be too uptight, so...
Ta-da!
I took the liberty of
bringing a new-and-improved
fallen maid set for you.
Nice, huh?
Check out how open
the décolletage is!
And this skirt'll be perfect
for showing off those legs.
[KANZAKI]
No! No, no, no, no, no!
Then what will you do?
Come on sweetie, you must
have some sort of plan!
After everything
that's happened,
you can't just phone it in.
A tilt of the head and
"I'm so grateful!"
That kind of "thank you"
isn't gonna cut it this time!
Yes, fine.
So... I...
I have to do something more.
But what would that be?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Try getting off your high horse.
Hey, I have a question!
What do you think those lovely
testaments to mammality are for?
Yes, those. Right there.
I mean your boobs, sweetie.
Why are they there?
And what are they for if you
don't know how to use them?
Wh-What?
Come on. Level with me.
You think this slow pace
is the best tactic?
Wait. What are
you talking about?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
I'm talking about Itsuwa.
The fact is, she
wouldn't think twice
about playing the sexy
fallen angel maid
if she needed to.
You're wrong! She'd never.
Listen!
You're starting to fall
way behind Itsuwa.
On a feminine level!
Really.
Are you going to let your
pride get the better of you?
You women and your
delicate sensibilities.
How dare you say
something like that to me?
Maybe you're not
truly cut out to lead
those little lost
sheep of yours.
Well, sweetie. What now?
What will you do?
[KAMIJO] Every inch of me
is covered in bruises.
But something like that won't
stop you from biting me, huh?
Hmph!
It's your own fault, Toma!
[door opens]
[KANZAKI]
Pardon me.
[GROUP]
Huh?!
[yells]
[ROMAN POPE]
I don't understand.
How in the world
was Acqua beaten?
[FIAMMA] It means the
opposition is progressing
more quickly than expected.
When did you emerge
from your bolt-hole,
Fiamma of the Right?
[FIAMMA]
That sort reaction won't do.
It makes it seem like
you're not cut out
for your exalted position.
[ROMAN POPE]
What are you planning?
[FIAMMA] First, we are
going to strike England.
[ROMAN POPE]
What?
[FIAMMA]
Don't you understand?
With the exception of England,
we've now managed to
bring nearly all of Europe
under our control.
We're going to contact
the other nations,
and with their help,
we'll dry England up.
I don't see how that will
do any substantial damage
to Academy City.
[FIAMMA] I'm not interested
in Academy City.
My focus is England
because it is there.
What do you mean by "it"?
[FIAMMA] Heh. Something we
will get our hands on.
Though it may require
exerting a great deal of power.
[ROMAN POPE]
It can't be.
Are you truly a follower
of the Church of the Cross?
You tell me.
Do you think that I am?
Damn you.
Now, now.
Such rough language is
hardly suitable for a pope.
You fool!
Do you really expect me
to sit back and do nothing?
Would you take me on?
An old man against the leader
of the Right Seat of God?
Old man, eh?
I call on the apostles
one to twelve,
and I beseech thee,
o infinite Lord!
May thy power be overflowing!
I am one who knows
its proper meaning.
I implore thee
that by this power,
my enemy be defeated!
You will remain idle here
for the next forty years.
You should use the experience
of this extended isolation
to sharpen your mind and
achieve some measure of wisdom.
[ROMAN POPE gasps]
[ROMAN POPE yells]
No!
That power, it can't be.
Yes. The right hand
symbolizes miracles, old man.
In Michael's right arm
is the mightiest of weapons.
I have within me the very
quintessence of miracles,
but I am unable to
use it to its fullest.
I lack the correct output
terminals to collect
and control it.
The power I wield in my
current state is nothing
compared to what it might be.
Be honest.
Wouldn't you want
to possess this?
The symbol of all miracles.
The Holy Right.
How could you?
I seek mastery of this weapon.
But it requires
overwhelming knowledge
beyond the domain of mankind
in order to control
overwhelming power.
[ROMAN POPE]
Index Librorum Prohibitorum!
Heh. Quite a delicate little
package for such an immense
store of knowledge,
wouldn't you say?
No! I won't allow this!
It's positively absurd that
you think you stand a chance
against me, but at least
this should be entertaining.
[FIAMMA]
He took all of that by himself?
Formidable bastard.
[ROMAN POPE coughs]
[VENTO] Ha! Took all of
that by yourself, huh?
You wouldn't have had to if
you'd simply forsaken this city.
Fiamma's revealed that
his target is in England.
--Go, quickly--
--Silence!
I don't take orders from you!
Although, if it coincides with
killing that rat bastard, well,
I suppose that I might
be willing to assist you.
[BOATMAN]
I have a report.
It appears that an internal
dispute has arisen
within the Roman Orthodoxy.
The pope was caught up in
it and is gravely injured.
From the amount of
magical force detected,
the damage to Vatican City
should be substantial,
but it's still being calculated.
Do-gooder.
However, I'd bet anything you
were smiling as you fought.
You do-good rascal.
[ALEISTER] It will take another
several hours to restore
the Underline information net.
I want you to process the
data that has been collected
just before shutdown.
Use the neural operational
status and AIM diffusion
field offset data to derive
the right arm's power
quality and quantity.
[overlapping voices]
[KAMIJO]
Under the archbishop's orders,
Index and I head for England.
An underhanded in-flight plot
spurs sorcerers into action.
Next time,
"Sky Bus Three-Six-Five."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.