[HAMAZURA panting]
[crash]
[HAMAZURA]
Damn it!
Of all the buildings
in the city,
why did they have
to choose this one?
[door opens]
I hate to do this,
but we gotta go.
I need to get into those
buildings with the private roo--
Too bad.
Hijacking an ex-member
of Academy City's
air defense won't work.
I'm surprised it isn't
assumed by now
that pilots carry weapons.
[phone buzzing]
What's wrong?
Don't you need to get that?
[phone buzzing]
[TAKITSUBO]
Hamazura.
Takitsubo, are you all right?
And where are you?
[TAKITSUBO]
I'm at our meetup place.
The private room.
I heard...
Please tell me you're not hurt.
[TAKITSUBO]
I'm fine.
[crash]
Takitsubo!
I'm okay.
I found a safe place
to take shelter for now.
Luckily it doesn't seem
like they've even noticed
I'm in here.
[HAMAZURA] Hold on,
then why do you sound like
you're so exhausted?
Just feeling a little worse now,
and I'm short of breath.
It's nothing that you need
to be worried about, though.
[HAMAZURA] Got it.
It's going to be all right.
I'll be over there soon.
I'm coming to save you.
I promise.
So just hang in there
a little while longer.
[TAKITSUBO]
No! Please don't!
You have to stay away.
I've counted ten of them.
All with submachine guns
and grenades at the ready.
If you come barging in now,
you won't be able to handle
them on your own.
So please stay where you are!
I can't. I'm coming.
You hear me? I'm on my way!
[HAMAZURA]
Please.
You can charge me
with whatever you want.
I wouldn't care if you dropped
me into the pits of Hell.
All I want to do
is rescue my friend.
Then I'm all yours.
Please help.
[PILOT 16A]
You should've said that sooner.
I've been hijacked.
The culprit is carrying a gun.
He's also got a small metal
drum filled with liquid.
Out of regard for the
lives of local residents,
I'm going to do what
he has asked of me.
But why?
I can't just say I'm
going off-route because
some kid insisted.
And I should warn you, they're
not going to let us land.
[HAMAZURA]
I know.
What's that?
[PILOT 16A]
An imitation tree, of course.
Having a real tree here would
hamper takeoffs and landings.
[HAMAZURA]
Yeah, that makes sense.
[HAMAZURA yells]
[HAMAZURA grunting]
--[HAMAZURA] Ow!
--[TERRORISTS] Huh?
[TERRORISTS grunt]
[HAMAZURA]
I'm coming, partner.
Even to the depths of Hell.
[TERRORIST 16B] When are we
supposed to join Stephanie?
Will she be giving us a signal?
[gunshot]
[TERRORIST 16A]
Is that B Team on the roof?
[TERRORISTS grunt]
[ACCELERATOR chuckles]
[TERRORIST 16C]
Hey. This is the 28th floor!
What do I care?
[TERRORISTS grunt]
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
--[gunshots]
--[TERRORISTS grunt]
Who're you?
That doesn't matter, does it?
[gunshots]
If you're serious about
keeping this city safe,
take more care in doing so.
Are you gonna
answer my question,
or do you just want
to die right here?
I'm Sugitani.
I pray we never
see each other again.
So please make every
effort to see we do not.
Tsuchimikado?
Yeah, I just cleaned
house on Spark Signal.
Now get up here and help
me check for any traps
or remaining injured.
[thud]
Huh?
[ACCELERATOR] Are you an
acute case or something?
Don't tell me
you're pregnant too.
I don't have time
to deal with that.
[HAMAZURA]
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Answer me! What are you
trying to do to Takitsubo?
Well, Level Five?
Does it feel good sneaking
around in the dark
terrorizing innocent people?
If you're seriously
planning to take something
precious away from me,
then this is the end for you,
Mr. Tough Guy!
Back off!
[ACCELERATOR chuckles]
I kinda like you.
You'd make a good villain.
[HAMAZURA grunts]
[ACCELERATOR]
It's over.
Stay down and
I'll leave you alone.
Move, I'll blow
right through you.
[HAMAZURA yells]
[ACCELERATOR]
Your life is in your hands.
What would you
like to do with it?
[HAMAZURA]
Isn't that obvious?
Not like I have a choice.
You don't have any
reason to back away
from this, do you? [coughs]
I'm not gonna be scarred
for life if I kill you
if that's what you're asking.
But of course,
that would be against
the rules, wouldn't it?
[HAMAZURA]
Takitsubo.
[ACCELERATOR]
What's it going to be, then?
If you'd like to continue,
I'll smash you
to a bloody pulp.
But if that kid is gonna
stand in our way,
we can go back to square one.
And this is an example
of a villainous aesthetic.
[HAMAZURA]
What's going on?
Have I made a mistake somehow?
Hamazura?
I'm so pathetic, aren't I?
I say I'm coming to save you,
then I end up like this.
What's even better,
I told off the guy who
probably saved your life.
Man, I really screwed that up.
[TAKITSUBO]
No, that's not true.
Hamazura, you came here
without any back-up
and risked your life--
I would never
call that pathetic.
[HAMAZURA]
You... wouldn't?
If you really believe that,
why are you crying?
[TAKITSUBO crying]
[HAMAZURA]
Nothing has changed.
I'm still here.
I'm the same Hamazura
I've always been.
I'm fine being called
a third-string punk.
But at the very least,
I wanna be the kind
of man who can preserve
her smile.
They're going ultra-wild
and tearing it up in there.
I may be too late to join them.
But I can ultra-help
with their escape plan.
[KINUHATA yelps]
[CROWD gasps]
Something like a shotgun
should be ultra-no-problem.
--[gunshots]
--[CROWD gasps]
Was that an automatic shotgun?
[STEPHANIE]
Yoo-hoo!
Let me guess, you must
be Saiai Kinuhata, right?
I'm so glad I decided
to use irrelevant former
Spark Signal members as bait.
My name is Stephanie
Gorgeouspalace.
I'm a sniper with a
mission to eliminate all
who've wronged Sunazara.
And yet you're still here.
If I were you, I'd be making
my peace right about now.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Every last person
who tries to find out anything
about DRAGON gets eliminated.
Heh. And that's exactly
the way Shiokishi wants it.
Fascinating.
I still wish we knew more about
this "DRAGON" business.
I have an opinion from
a magic perspective.
Typically when you hear
the word "dragon,"
it evokes a certain imagery
of religious metaphors.
Like angels, for example.
Angels?
On September 30th,
angel wings appeared
in Academy City.
The name of the virus
that bastard Kihara
was using was also "Angel."
Perhaps "Angel" and "DRAGON"
are tied together somehow.
DRAGON is connected
to Last Order!
So, does that mean
there's something more
going on with that experiment?
Is this all part
of someone's plan?
It's that Shiokishi bastard.
I suppose that means
now we've all become
targets of his.
Well, the good news is that
the enemy has been revealed.
Which means the priority is
to find out what the lineup is.
[ACCELERATOR gasps]
[ACCELERATOR]
The electricity's been cut off?
This is bad.
I can't collect my thoughts.
[footsteps]
[ACCELERATOR]
You again.
Did you know that in a pinch,
the body will continue
to work on its own?
Which means the man who
saved my teacher's life
didn't have to die.
Who's putting you up to this?
Is it another one
of Shiokishi's traps?
It's true.
You and I are both products
of the same profession.
But still.
Regardless of how
criminal it may seem,
the fact remains that
you saved someone
who is dearer to me
than life itself.
I owed you this.
So now I'm paying you back.
[ACCELERATOR]
Just keep driving, okay?
[HIGH SCHOOL BOY 15A]
Where are you planning to go?
[ACCELERATOR] I have to kill
that bastard Shiokishi.
When he finds out
he didn't finish me off,
he's gonna take advantage
of the most vulnerable
weakness I have.
But there's more than just
her I must fight to protect.
I have to protect
everything to fight him.
Either that, or...
[ACCELERATOR chuckles]
[ACCELERATOR]
There's an easier way.
Early bird catches the worm.
For someone as
drenched in blood as me,
doing it like that instead
might be more appropriate.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Listen close, Accelerator,
head straight for
the observatory in
School District 21.
Huh? Why, is that where
Shiokishi's secret hiding place
is or something?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
No.
But this fight in
particular is gonna require
some additional
political preparation.
We need to find someone
who has the same kind of pull
as the governing board.
Know anyone?
I sure don't.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Monaka Oyafune.
She's hosting a stargazing
party for all the children
who were being held
by the terrorists.
She's got the biggest heart of
anyone on the governing board.
I don't like taking
advantage of kindness,
but she owes us one.
[SECRETARY 16A]
Please leave.
Ms. Oyafune no longer
wants to live a life
that leads her into
both light and darkness.
You should understand that.
As someone who lives
in the world of darkness,
you know how
difficult it can be.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Sorry to bother you.
I do have one question, though.
Do you have any idea what
happened to Oyafune?
Has to do with her daughter.
Huh?
During the time when she
was promoting regulations
that would control the
export of weapons,
she received an unfired
pistol addressed to her.
A photo of her daughter
was also in that package.
Ultimately, nothing came of it.
But I suspect it was Shiokishi.
He is quite the war hawk,
after all.
It was after that that Ms.
Oyafune left the front lines.
If she gets involved
with you, then once again...
I get it.
[MONAKA]
Excuse me.
Who is this gentleman?
I'm nobody, lady.
I was just asking
for directions.
[SECRETARY 16A] You must have
had some idea that this would
be the case,
and yet you still came here.
Tell me what's happened!
[ACCELERATOR]
What difference does it make?
No matter what
trouble I may endure
with that son of
a bitch Shiokishi,
I'm pretty certain you're
better off not knowing about it.
I'm sorry.
[ACCELERATOR]
Don't be. It's my problem.
I should have just gone
it alone to begin with.
After the fight with
that bastard is over,
I'll be treated
like a terrorist.
But so what?
I've already made up my mind.
And what's more,
even if I turn that kid
I'm trying to
protect against me,
I'm still going to keep
fighting for her safety.
It doesn't change
my obligations.
[BOY VICTIM 15A]
Hey! Don't I know you?
You're that hero from
earlier, aren't you?
What are you doing out here?
That's none of
your business, kid.
You're going somewhere
to fight again, aren't you?
You're off to save more
people, like you did before.
I want you to take me with you!
I'll fight by your side!
You gotta be kidding me,
you little brat.
Can you even hear the words
coming out of your mouth?
I just know that
wherever you're going
is probably gonna be
super dangerous.
If there are people who are
in as much trouble as I was,
then I want to help
them like you helped me!
[ACCELERATOR]
That's not necessary.
An almighty Level Five
doesn't need help.
Come on!
I don't want to stay here
and watch Academy City
get turned over to all
those stupid cowards!
--[GUARD 16A] All right.
--[TEACHER 16A] Let's go.
[MONAKA]
It's true, then?
You are planning
to fight him, aren't you?
Be honest.
Ms. Oyafune!
[MONAKA] Who exactly were these
"cowards" that young boy
was speaking of?
Does that refer to the darkness
that lurks in the city,
or to those who know
of this darkness
but give up the fight?
What am I supposed
to do at this point?
Nobody cares.
This is your life, isn't it?
You get to decide.
[SECRETARY 16A gasps]
Ms. Oyafune?
[MONAKA] My eyes have
finally been opened.
I've decided on the
best course of action.
We're going to
Shiokishi's place.
[HAMAZURA] Did you get
in touch with Kinuhata?
Not yet.
My calls aren't going through.
I wonder if something happened.
We waited as long as we
could for her to show up.
So then... How are we
going to find her?
Let's not forget,
she's a tough Level Four.
She's stronger than us.
It'll take something
substantial to kill her.
[CROWD yelling]
[HAMAZURA]
Now what's going on?
That looks pretty
substantial to me!
Hamazura, over there.
She could be in
that underground mall.
[HAMAZURA]
This is such a mess.
What now?
Keep going or turn back?
Wait. Look.
[HAMAZURA]
Kinuhata!
Ultra-hit the deck now!
Darn, so close.
I figured that since your
ability uses nitrogen,
it might be smart to do
something about the air.
You see, there's a
momentary vacuum
created by the blast that
I thought would be perfect
for pumping you full of lead.
Go on! Both of you,
ultra-get out of here!
Get down!
[gunshots]
[SHIOKISHI] The board
authorization system has been
activated?
So she's decided to use
that here, has she?
What would you like me to do?
It appears that her
activation has neutralized
the political defense
functionality.
Also...
[SHIOKISHI]
GROUP? Why, that vixen!
What do you think the chances
are that she'll actually
resort to using
hardline measures?
[SHIOKISHI] It does have
something to do with DRAGON,
after all.
They're certain to be coming.
So we will engage them here.
This is all-out war!
[SUGITANI]
Yes, sir.
Oh, great. You see that thing
on top? It's an AIM jammer.
Control over our abilities is
about to be pretty restricted.
Ha.
He knew we would come
and already covered
his bases against us.
So, then, what is
our plan of action?
[ACCELERATOR]
Isn't it obvious?
We continue to break
straight through.
[ACCELERATOR]
Let's go.
Tsuchimikado, you stay
here and stand guard.
Ms. Oyafune, your job will
be to speak with Shiokishi.
One on one.
Accelerator and I will
stay just ahead of you
and break down the
walls as we go along.
But be prepared to
stand right in the line
of fire at the very end.
[ACCELERATOR]
Musujime!
It isn't working.
I think something else
must have happened
on the other side of this wall.
So you're useless.
[SUGITANI] Might I challenge
you two to a fight?
You don't listen to
instructions, do you?
I said I didn't want
to see you again.
And yet, here you are
walking straight toward me.
I said to make every
effort to prevent it.
Clearly you haven't.
[ACCELERATOR] Why don't you tell
us what you know about DRAGON?
[dart whizzes]
[SUGITANI]
Poison.
Musujime has the ability
to pass through walls,
so naturally that makes
her a much higher priority
than you.
[ACCELERATOR] Are you gonna
tell me who you are?
Who am I?
A descendent of the Koga.
I'm part of a band
of dastardly spies
who have been doing
this sort of work
in the name of justice
since the times of old.
Oyafune is being handled.
Once she is eliminated,
the rest of Academy
City's collective power
can be mobilized, and that
will be the end of you.
And then, once we have
Last Order secured
as our final card,
it'll be over.
[MONAKA] What I'd like
to request of you is
quite simple, really.
Henceforth, the following
must be changed.
I want you to permanently
remove the stipulations
in your plans that allow
you to incorporate
and consume the lives
of others at will.
That's all.
This is something everyone
else has observed
as a matter of course.
I'd also like you to tell
me more of what you know
about DRAGON.
[SHIOKISHI] What makes
you think I know more?
It's just something that
the fellows in GROUP
requested of me to ask.
[SHIOKISHI]
I see.
I am doing nothing more
than carrying out matters
point by point that
are necessary to keep
Academy City safe.
"DRAGON" is just a word
that carries the virtue
of sounding dangerous.
You might even call it barbaric.
But that's because
you don't know
what's behind DRAGON.
From what you say,
I understand it well.
Too well.
See, I too carry out actions
that could be called barbaric.
[SHIOKISHI]
Are we at an impasse?
We both wish to
protect Academy City,
but that seems to mean
different things to each of us.
[SHIOKISHI]
I see.
That thought never
crossed your mind, did it?
You didn't think
about the possibility
that we might have
some things in common--
such as taking steps
ahead of time to defend
our own lives.
Must've caught you by surprise.
[SHIOKISHI]
Wh-What?!
Mitsuki Unabara!
Is that really the name
you wanna go with?
I was so sure you were
gonna call me "Etzali."
Oh, well. My mistake.
That coward...
So then where's
the real Oyafune?
Does this mean she's
around somewhere
watching from a safe distance?
That's a very good question.
The talisman I use is actually
made with live human skin.
Knowing that, Ms. Oyafune
still didn't hesitate
to give a sample.
You call her a coward,
but peeling ten centimeters
of skin from her arm must
have been pretty painful.
Now, why don't you tell me
more about DRAGON?
Unless of course
you're curious about the pain
Ms. Oyafune endured?
Maybe you could
see for yourself
what that "coward" went through.
[SHIOKISHI grunts]
Minobe!
Here's a helpful tip.
Always have two
security outfits on hand
in case someone in proximity
decides to betray you.
If it comes down to it,
they can always end
up killing each other.
[chuckles]
Huh?!
What is this?
Why? Why have all other security
guards besides you two
been killed?
[gasps]
[UNABARA]
It can't be!
[MINOBE]
And why not?
Did you not consider
the possibility that others
may have infiltrated the
darker side of Academy City
just as you have done?
[UNABARA]
Técpatl! And Tochtli!
[KAMIJO] It appears in
the form of Fuse=KAZAKIRI.
The aeon passes
from Osiris to Horus.
"Do what thou wilt shall
be the whole of the Law."
Next time, "DRAGON."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.