[MISAKA WORST gasps]
[MISAKA WORST]
The bleeding has stopped.
But why?
Misaka should not have
survived that attack.
Impossible!
There's no way he
would save Misaka!
What's wrong? [grunts]
What reason do you have
to protect this Misaka?!
[MISAKA WORST yells, grunts]
[ACCELERATOR laughing]
Vento.
It's Fiamma. I don't like the
way he does things. Period.
He seemed to disappear
quite suddenly.
Do you know where he went?
Yeah.
I have a pretty good guess.
Maybe you've convinced yourself
that you're not doing it
for your own self-satisfaction.
But when all is said and done,
will your hypothetically noble
act actually be her salvation?
I can't wait for the
judgment to come down.
[LESSAR] I can't tell
what you're hiding,
but whatever it is...
Remember that you didn't
stop dead in your tracks
when difficult
situations came up.
You still continued to
move forward and give it
everything you had,
no matter what.
And as a result, you've saved
a number of people's lives.
Take some credit.
I mean, you even managed
to stop the coup
back in Britain.
What I'm saying is
you've lived a life
that you can be proud of.
That's nice of you.
But...
...whatever my intentions
may have been,
the decisions I made
affected Index.
And the fact is...
I'm not the one who gets to
decide what's best for her.
[TANK DRIVER 20A chuckling]
Just keep on running!
[CHILD 19A gasps]
[CITIZEN 19A, CHILD 19A gasp]
[HAMAZURA yelling]
[yelling]
Go! Now!
I'm sorry.
I hate that I'm the one who
dragged you into all this.
Now is not a good
time for apologies!
Besides, you've given
Takitsubo a spot
in your underground shelter.
Consider this payback.
[HAMAZURA]
Why're they stopping?
They're not.
[HAMAZURA, DIGURV grunting]
They really do enjoy
killing people, don't they?
At this rate, everyone in the
village will be dead soon.
[HAMAZURA]
Not if we can help it.
Weapons.
Don't you have anything
stored away for emergencies?
We don't have anything
that would cut through
that kind of armor.
I think you do!
The landmines.
You said you were
saving them so you could
turn them over to an NGO, right?
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Can we really hold the line?
[CARISSA] I wouldn't exactly
call this a defensive war
of attrition.
It's more of a mop-up battle
to prepare for our attack.
Glastonbury,
the mobile fortress.
By taking control of the area
around it and claiming it
as British territory,
we are able to dramatically
extend Curtana's range of usage.
And it truly is a larger-scale
magical item for invasions.
The intent of the enemy doesn't
even matter in this case,
don't you agree?
Yes.
[CARISSA] There's one
more thing I'd like to try.
[yells]
Somebody please help me!
If those evil
French bastards win,
I'll be captured and
violated before I die!
[BRITISH SORCERERS yelling]
We must keep
Princess Carissa safe!
That's more like it. Where
was this kind of enthusiasm
when you first
started fighting?
[KNIGHT LEADER]
That's right.
Could you please put me
in touch with Queen Elizard?
As soon as possible.
I want to ask her permission
to punish Princess Carissa.
[CARISSA]
What do you think you're doing?
Come on, you know
how my mother can be.
She would probably bestow
all of Curtana Second's power
to you just so you
could humiliate me.
[FEMME FATALE]
Second Princess Carissa?
I thought that was you.
It's The holy maiden
of Versailles.
[CARISSA] Your body has
undergone conditioning
at the visceral level.
It's prevented you
from being able to live
outside the confines
of Versailles.
Your power's been curtailed
by idiotic French heavyweights
who fear you.
Therefore, victory is ours!
If you were able to
come out here directly,
the battle might have
ended differently.
[FEMME FATALE chuckles]
[CARISSA grunts]
[FEMME FATALE] Actually,
I am able to move about.
And that will become known as
France's mightiest move to date.
[KANZAKI gasps]
What's that?
Don't tell me you're wielding a
fragment of Curtana Second!
It's a result of
my fight with Mother.
During which, Curtana
Original and Curtana Second
endured a heavy-handed clash,
and this is the result.
Like you, I am also
free to move about,
and that is the greatest
move Britain ever made!
--[KAMIJO grunts]
--[LESSAR] What the--?
[DRIVER 20A]
Look! Over there!
[ACCELERATOR laughing]
That's it! I
can't hold it in any longer!
It's gonna take more than
that kid's precious smile
to stop it now!
[laughing]
I wanna see every last
inch of it destroyed!
[laughing]
I wanna mow down
everything in existence!
[laughing]
I want to rid this world
of people who would create
such a thing!
Put an end to the jerks
who benefit from it.
Forever!
And I mean all of them!
Every last disgusting one!
[laughing]
[KAMIJO]
Accelerator!
No way.
Why're you here?
Tell me. Tell me!
Tell me why!
Well, if it isn't the so-called
hero who gave enough of a damn
to save all those sisters.
What the hell are
you talking about?
[ACCELERATOR]
But what about the kid, huh?
She's never done
anything to hurt anyone
in her entire existence!
So what sense does it
make for someone like her
to suffer like that?!
[yelling]
[KAMIJO grunts]
[LESSAR whimpering]
[KAMIJO yells]
[TANK DRIVER 20A laughs]
Where are you hiding,
little kitties?
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
[laughs]
We don't know which
route they're using,
and there's not a lot
of time to set things up.
[HAMAZURA]
There's not much else we can do.
So toss them like grenades
when they get close.
Oh, you're heading
my way first, are you?
That's fine with me!
I'm ready for it.
Come at me any way you like!
[HAMAZURA grunts]
[DIGURV]
Did that do it?
[PRIVATEER DRIVER 20A]
Damn it, move!
[HAMAZURA]
It's chilly out today, huh?
That's my favorite kind of
weather for a barbecue.
It's not over.
[PRIVATEER PILOT 20A laughs]
I'll blast ya full of holes!
Damn it!
[ACCELERATOR laughing]
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
[KAMIJO yelling]
[ACCELERATOR yelling]
You're supposed
to be the big hero!
If you've got special
powers no one else has,
then share the damn wealth!
Why not use some to
help that kid, huh?!
How crazy is it that a
villainous bastard like me
is the only one who's
ever cared enough
to stick up for her
all this time?
Just look at me! There's
no way I could be a hero!
I don't save anyone! Ever!
When I wanna fix something,
I do it with blood and pain!
I shouldn't have to
go through this crap!
You're the damn hero!
It's your job to
rush to the rescue!
[ACCELERATOR coughs]
If damn heroes would
do their job and show up
when they're supposed to,
stupid mistakes like this
never would've been
possible in the first place!
That kid might be okay!
If you had been there,
she wouldn't have had to
suffer like that!
You're kidding me.
What the hell?!
Hero or not,
that should've killed you!
[KAMIJO]
What's a hero to you anyway?
An average Level Zero like me?
Do I really look like I'm
that big of a deal to anyone?
Good guys? Bad guys?
Come on, grow up!
Are you saying that
in order to help someone,
you have to meet
specific qualifications?
If someone you know is crying
and you wish they weren't,
or if someone struggling
to hold on needs help
but doesn't have
the strength to ask...
Isn't that reason enough?
What more do you
need to step up?
You want special permission
or some kind of label?
It's no skin off your
nose to try and help.
If they're important,
what's stopping you?
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[grunts]
I don't know what it is
you're afraid of or how badly
you've been burned
by others in the past,
but if you wanted
to protect that kid,
then you should've just done
so with your head held high!
You have the strength
and ability to keep her safe
right now!
Be proud of that!
[KAMIJO grunts]
[KAMIJO]
The choice is yours.
You can continue protecting
her on your own.
You can run away and
leave it for someone else.
Or you can ask for help
and we can do this together!
[ACCELERATOR]
I don't--
I am not going to make
this decision for you.
Call it arrogance or
whatever you want.
You're the only one who can
decide if she's worth it.
No one else can
tell you what to do!
[ACCELERATOR]
I wanted to defend her.
No matter the cost.
I had to do something.
So I rushed down the only
path I knew I could take.
I chose the path of evil, and I
excelled at living that life.
However...
In the end, it was the guy
who never once had to question
whether he was good or evil
who managed to come through.
Turned out that he was
the strongest one of all.
I can't protect her
with pure evil.
Fighting for those suffering
from inexcusable savagery.
And giving everything you have
to stop unnecessary tears.
These are what I would call
very admirable actions, indeed.
[PRIVATEER PILOTS gasp]
[ACQUA]
I am Aqua of the Rear.
May I be so presumptuous
as to offer you a hand?
[weapons clash]
What did you just say?
[CARISSA]
The Kremlin Report.
It's Russia's first-priority
national defense manual.
If the mainland is
invaded by force,
and the nuclear launch
facilities are about to be
taken over,
do you have any idea
what means they'll adopt
in order to prevent
that from happening?
Give up?
They'll disperse a
bacterial wall to act
as an airborne killer!
There won't be a single
evacuation order issued.
Not for the Russian soldiers
who are working in the facility,
or the people who live nearby.
The manual's sole priority
is to ensure the security
of the nuclear launch sites.
It doesn't matter how
many times you brag
about how just your cause is.
The fact remains that
you're using French soil
as a springboard to
intervene in Russia.
France has enjoyed
many benefits from growth
under the protection of
the Roman Orthodox Church.
So now we can't afford to
cast aside their orders.
Everyone knows the
truth about this war.
We're all very much aware
that it wasn't caused
by the Roman Orthodoxy,
but by Fiamma.
And now we have the
opportunity to avoid
a worst-case scenario.
So what'll it be?
You know, there was a time
when I considered France
to be my archenemy.
Hard to believe they can really
be this pathetic and useless.
[KUROKO]
Hey, Sissy!
Look!
Wait, why are you packing?
[KUROKO] Can you at least
tell me what your plan is?
You're not going there, are you?
Uh...
But why? It's a war zone.
And how do you even
expect to get in?
Oh. Um... Well...
There are ways.
[MUGINO humming]
I can't wait to see
you again, Hamazura.
[ACCELERATOR]
"Index Librorum Prohibitorum."
Welcome to the Elizalina
Alliance of Independent Nations.
[ACCELERATOR] Maybe it is
all connected somehow.
[KAMIJO] I was probably too
hard on Accelerator back there.
I don't get shuffling around
looking for a logical reason
to help.
I don't do it
because it's right.
The only reason I helped
her is because I wanted to.
[LESSAR laughs]
One minute you're stressed out,
and the next you bounce back!
That must keep you pretty busy.
[KAMIJO] I realize that
I'm a real lowlife.
I'm a worthless jerk who's
been deceiving Index.
But as bad as I may be,
I know for sure it's not
Fiamma I should be bowing to.
Well, now.
I'd say it's a perfect time
to begin the delightful
Project B'Tselem.
[KAMIJO]
The project kicks off at last.
The earth shakes,
the skies turn pitch-black,
and strange objects rise.
The light of
destruction descends.
Next time,
"The Star of Bethlehem."
When science and magic cross
paths, a story is born.