[REPORTERS chattering]
All right.
Now we just take the domestic
flight to London from here.
Easy enough.
[INDEX]
Toma...!
[INDEX growling]
[KAMIJO]
Wha--?!
You never told me if
I was getting beef or fish
and then I never
got anything at all!
It's been ages and I'm
about to collapse here!
I'll die if I don't eat soon!
[BOTH yell]
Yes, it has been too long.
Uh... Hold on.
What is the fallen angel
sexy maid doing here?
[VILIAN]
Yes, I see.
Being right after
a terrorist incident,
I understand that
they have quite a bit
of investigating to do.
I only ask that the liquid
food is still distributed
to the households in need
as quickly as possible.
[SERVANT 11A]
Princess Vilian?
The leaders of the
Knights and the Puritans,
as well as our young guests
from Academy City,
have arrived at the palace.
It is nearly time
for their audience.
Please prepare yourself.
I understand.
William.
[KAMIJO]
Oh, wow.
So... I don't suppose
you happen to know
why we were called here.
[KANZAKI] Tsuchimikado was
supposed to do your orientation.
Did he not?
Not unless orientation
includes gassing us
and leaving us at the airport.
[KNIGHT LEADER]
You're here.
[KANZAKI]
Knight Leader.
[KNIGHT LEADER] You've been
brought here to Buckingham
Palace to participate
in a strategy meeting.
Though, officially,
it will be called an audience.
As such, I would have hoped
you'd be dressed more formally.
More formally?
[coughs]
[INDEX] Now when you
say "strategy meeting,"
what sort of strategizing
will we be doing?
We want to discuss the
possibility that magic
was involved in the
recent Eurotunnel blast.
Her Majesty can
answer your questions.
Like the queen?
[INDEX yawns]
[ELIZARD]
Oh! Dresses are a pain!
Can I just wear a track suit?
One moment, please.
[ELIZARD] Oh! Can't you at
least knock before entering?
[KNIGHT LEADER]
I do apologize, but first...
This is official business!
How dare you ask to show up
in a track suit again,
you gormless prat!
Now that my
tummy's finally full,
I'm feeling a little sleepy.
[KAMIJO] But the main
event's about to start!
[INDEX whiness]
The queen has seen the light.
We're ready now.
Please, won't you come in?
Sword?
[ELIZARD]
It's not just a sword.
It's a royal sword
known as Curtana.
Thank you for coming.
Please, join us down here.
[KAMIJO] Is that sword
some kind of big deal?
It's extremely powerful.
And whomever possesses it
can obtain the same quality
of power as the
archangel Michael.
Archangel?
[INDEX] That's right.
He's not only the strongest
and most important
of the angels--
he's their leader as well.
[KAMIJO]
Oh, wow!
Also, if by some twist of fate
this were to be destroyed,
no one would be that upset.
You see, this beauty is
actually Curtana Second.
Unfortunately, just
telling me the name
doesn't really explain anything.
It means this is the second one.
The Curtana Original
was the first to appear,
but it's gone missing somehow.
So even if this
Curtana were to break,
a new one would
immediately emerge.
[RIMEA] For goodness sake,
that's absolutely untrue.
Curtana Second is a second sword
and was crafted
with great precision.
But the method of
forging it has been lost,
so we couldn't make
a third or fourth so easily.
That would be the
First Princess Riméa.
f you would have
asked one of my men--
No. I would have come
to get you, Princess.
Oh, no, we can't have that!
What good would it
do to make myself
vulnerable to deception?
You think I'd enjoy being
stabbed in the back?
I will never place
my trust in the hands
of those who know me.
Feeling dark and gloomy
again, are we, sister?
If you refuse to have
faith in anything,
then you may as well end
your life here and now.
We'd all be better off.
[KAMIJO]
Sister?
I'm the Second
Princess, Carissa.
Perhaps you should study
your history, young man.
Don't tell me.
Vilian's here too?
My younger sister,
the third princess.
Quite boring, wouldn't you say?
Now then, the others
will be gathering soon.
I suppose it's time we
should be dashing off.
[KAMIJO]
Huh?
[ELIZARD] There are occasions
when fewer people
in a shorter amount of
time can be more effective
in carrying out a discussion.
Then what was the point
of inviting the two of us
out here in the first place?
Really?
I've got the queen and
some princesses here.
With so many famous
people in one place,
I feel like I should
take a picture.
Um, can I help you?
I thought I heard you say
you wanted to take a photo.
[RIMEA] You didn't think
I'd allow you to leave me
out of the picture, did you?
I'll move in a little closer.
Here, as long as
we're taking photos,
I would prefer it if
you would allow me
to stage it properly.
[VILIAN]
Would you mind if I joined you?
How dare you take a
photograph without including
the ruler of the country
you are visiting!
Have you no manners--?
[ELIZARD] The topic of
discussion will be France.
France, yes.
And more specifically,
I'd like to discuss
the Eurotunnel blast.
I've made a decision.
This was an act of subversion
by the French government.
[CARISSA]
Really? Do you have proof?
[ELIZARD] That is the
reason I summoned the List
of Prohibited Books.
If a French Roman
Orthodox spell was used
in the destruction,
she should be able
to correctly identify that.
We should change
our perspective.
This isn't a quarrel
between Britain and France.
It appears to be a great power
struggle between Britain,
Academy City, Rome, and Russia.
What's more,
presently, Britain
is being isolated.
That's true.
However, it is not
the only issue at hand.
In the thick of this
latest hijacking incident,
I came across a fact
that was quite concerning.
[KAMIJO]
Wait, concerning how?
[ELIZARD] We enlisted
Necessarius's help
to create an illusion spell.
We later found
traces of something
that had caused it
to jam and fail.
What troubles me most
is that evidence shows
the source of this jamming
came from Scotland,
right here in
the United Kingdom.
So we have more than
just our outside enemies.
As if it wasn't
enough of a headache
dealing with Britain and
France squabbling as they are.
Now you're saying we have
independent terrorists
inside the country, too? Blast.
The identity of the
terrorists has been revealed.
Their organization's
name is "New Light."
It's comprised of four members.
They also appear to have just
completed an archeological dig.
I wonder if they mean to
bring whatever they dug up
back to London in
order to carry on
with some sort of
subversive activity.
If so, there are two things
we must do immediately.
First, deal with the
external threat from France
by determining the true cause
of the Eurotunnel blast.
Then determine affiliation
of the sorcerer
who is the internal threat
so that they can be
eliminated if necessary.
Heading up the
Eurotunnel investigation
for our external threat
will be the knights.
The Puritans will take
the lead in scrutinizing
British sorcerer societies
in order to find
the internal threat.
However, the List
of Prohibited Books
will be acting
separately to help
with the investigation here.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Um... May I ask what
I'm supposed to do?
There you go again!
You have this terrible habit
of wanting to be involved
in every incident
that comes along!
[CARISSA]
Really? I don't see why not.
Necessarius appears to be
pretty shorthanded these days.
I disagree.
I don't think it's advisable to
expose civilians to such danger.
Yes, I see your point.
There's no need to force
civilians to help us.
He should stay back until
the situation is resolved.
Lucky me! I can just sit here
and relax until you're done.
Now then. Should anyone not
serving the national interest
run up a bill during
their stay here,
we will request payment
for those expenses
at a later date.
You don't mind, do you?
[ELIZARD] I must say, it's quite
the bargain when you think of it
as having two or three
suites to yourself
at a gaudy five-star hotel.
It would be my honor to
work alongside all of you
for the sake of British peace.
[BAYLOUPE] Tell me, does it
feel like the game is on yet?
Lancis, you are our goalkeeper.
[LANCIS giggles]
I'm ready for it!
This magic is tickling me!
[FLORIS] Whatever, our half
will strike hard and fast.
We'll get this done quickly.
[BAYLOUPE]
Hey, Lessar,
You haven't forgotten that
you're a part of that half,
have you?
If you screw this up,
you'll answer to me.
I'm not going to.
But since we're
picking positions,
I'd like to be a forward.
[LANCIS] Are you finished
getting the Skidbladnirs ready?
After all it took
to dig that up,
we need to be careful
with its container, too.
[LESSAR]
Yes, I understand.
We're transforming
Britain today, aren't we?
Big day for "New Light" members!
[KAMIJO] You know, I never
thought I'd run into you.
Well, a lot has happened
since we last spoke.
Let's just say I
made a little deal.
And now, I'm using my skills
for Britain instead, you see?
[KAMIJO yelps]
All right. Now I just carry
the suitcase into position,
and then wait
here for the signal.
What the--?
Uh... This is my suitcase.
I think yours is
the one down here.
Uh... Oh, so sorry, miss.
[LESSAR]
That was close.
Wait. Which one is that?
[LESSAR gasps]
Everybody freeze, now!
[KAMIJO yells]
[ORIANA] Sounds to me like
one of them just screwed up.
[KAMIJO]
What's going on there?
[ORIANA] An obvious
explosion of suspiciousness.
[LESSAR]
Let's see, which one is it?
This one?
No, this one!
First, we clear the area.
And then, we handle
the other thing.
[KAMIJO gasps]
Kinda overdoing it, aren't you?
[ORIANA] On the contrary,
this could be bad.
Hey, wait!
[LESSAR]
You don't mind, do you?
[KAMIJO yells]
[LESSAR grunts]
You're kidding me, right?
[LESSAR chuckles]
[LESSAR yells]
Why'd I do that?
I hid behind the
most important thing!
[KAMIJO]
Hey, Oriana.
I get the feeling that
we should be going after
that rectangular case.
I think you're right.
And if it also happens
to be a magical item,
wouldn't it be interesting
if you were to punch it
with your right hand?
Yeah, that's a good call!
I can't afford to
be outdone right now!
[glass breaks]
[KAMIJO]
Damn it.
How are we s'posed
to follow that?
Easy. We don't.
[LESSAR]
Help me!
Help me, please!
[BAYLOUPE]
Well, worst-case scenario,
I'll make sure at least
one of these activates.
[ITSUWA]
English Puritan Church.
0th Parish. Necessarius.
I need you to come with us
to the Tower of London.
Would you like to know
the charges against you?
No, that's all right.
I have no intention
of getting caught
until I can activate this case.
--Itsuwa!
--I got it!
[ITSUWA]
Your spear.
From its magical glyph,
I'm sensing it's of
the Thunder God, Thor.
Don't be so naïve to
immediately think it's Mjöllnir.
It's not.
The thunder god has used
other weapons before--
at least once.
After dissecting the accounts,
we unearthed
these magical items.
The Steel Gloves.
As it turns out,
these weapons are much
easier for women to use!
[ITSUWA]
Is it grasping something?
Like wind from the air?
Dust particles?
[ITSUWA yells]
Have you had enough yet?
'Cause I can keep going.
But I think I'll change it up
and use Gjallarhorn next.
Unless you want to
be turned into cinders,
you should stay
right where you are.
This thing is about to alter
the course of British history.
You can expect to see all sorts
of changes start to come about.
Under whose orders
are you doing this?
Is it France?
Is it the Roman Orthodoxy?
France or the Roman Orthodoxy?
Right.
[CARISSA] As it turns out,
our sister didn't come.
What's Riméa doing?
I don't know. She's just
always had a difficult time
trusting others.
I recognize that France
has been involved
in a series of incidents.
But that doesn't mean
the Roman Orthodoxy
didn't influence them somehow.
Is seeking military
action against France
the only dialogue
we can hope to have?
[CARISSA] If you'd like
to see it go a different way,
you'd better come up
with a specific solution.
Our sister is the brains.
I specialize in war.
And you, in virtue.
Perhaps it's your
calling to come up with
a more effective method
of dealing with this.
Sister.
[CARISSA]
Brace yourselves.
We're nearly to Folkestone.
[BAYLOUPE]
Ridiculous.
That idiot Lessar has
managed to mess up
everything somehow.
This is supposed
to be a direct line.
Why's it curving?
[ITSUWA]
You might learn something.
There are many magical
training grounds in London.
[BAYLOUPE]
It can't be.
[BAYLOUPE gasps]
[AGNESE]
According to our intel,
New Light is made
up of four people.
If there are still
three more of them,
this could be a
bit of a problem.
[ITSUWA] I think I have some
good news on that front.
[ITSUWA]
Two to go.
[alarm ringing]
Man, you like playing
it fast and loose!
[LESSAR]
By all appearances,
you are neither a sorcerer
nor are you British.
What reason could
someone like you
possibly have for pursuing me?
Whatever the case may be,
not being British
means you're instantly out!
You have no stake in this!
[KAMIJO]
Meaning what?
[LESSAR] You don't really
need to understand.
All I can tell you is that
we intend to steer Britain
in a different direction
right at the breaking point.
Damn it!
[LESSAR grunts]
Don't tell me.
It's tempered glass.
A fall from this
height would kill me.
[KAMIJO laughs]
Will it be death
or apprehension?
Apprehension! Uh...
Wah! I'm gonna die!
[LESSAR] If you don't catch me,
I'm the one who's gonna die!
[screams]
[KAMIJO]
Huh?
That's a major point deduction!
I'm going after
her now, all right?
[KAMIJO]
"Skidbladnir"?
[AGNESE] Yes. The cases they're
carrying with them right now.
Its effect as a magical item
is to take whatever
is placed in Case A
and teleport it to Case B,
Case C, or Case D.
The item can be passed to
anyone within 100 kilometers.
So they can pass around
an important object
as if they're playing
a game of lacrosse?
[AGNESE]
I suppose so.
But be aware that
it could be a bomb
or some other weapon.
Yeah, I got it.
[AGNESE] New Light is
made up of four members.
Two of them have
already been brought down.
The main item must
be in one of the two
remaining members' cases.
So hurry.
[KAMIJO yells]
[KAMIJO]
Are you kidding me?!
[grunts]
[LESSAR]
No!
[KAMIJO yells]
[BOTH yelp]
[KAMIJO]
We know what it is you're after.
We've already caught the others.
[LESSAR]
Sure, but it doesn't matter
if you haven't figured out where
Lancis is hiding, does it?
The three of us
are acting as relays.
You see, all I have to do is
pass it to another member
and our mission will succeed.
[KAMIJO]
Relays?
[LESSAR] I can't believe it
never crossed your mind
from the moment you
found out these were
mass produced.
You never imagined there'd be
a fifth Skidbladnir, did you?
Guess not.
Who'd you send it to?
Tell me who's carrying
the fifth case!
[LESSAR]
The objective has been achieved,
but I lost the race
in the process.
And I'm okay with that.
So if you're going to shut me
up, now would be the best time.
[ORIANA]
A sniper?
[KAMIJO] Damn it!
Oriana, call an ambulance!
[ORIANA]
Robin Hood?
[KAMIJO]
What is that?
[ORIANA] A magical item
used by the knights
for long-range sharpshooting.
It was developed by a
well-known military unit
working directly under Carissa.
And if that same unit is
involved in silencing New Light,
then that means...
It means you know
what we were transporting.
Curtana Original.
It's the ceremonial sword
used in coronations
once lost to history.
The greatest magical item
in the United Kingdom.
Much stronger and far
superior to Curtana Second.
No sword is worthier
or more perfectly suited
to transform Britain.
Alert every knight hidden
throughout the land!
Be ready to move quickly!
Let the invasion commence!
Curtana Original is
now in our hands!
Those who do not wish to
see their country befouled
are invited to rise up
with me, Carissa,
as I am now your
new head of state!
This is the start of a
new United Kingdom.
We will improve whatever
we see as necessary.
And whatever we don't need
will be destroyed!
[KAMIJO]
An invasion by the knights?
Chaos brought about
by all this fighting
will be slashed by
one man's sword.
His name is William Orwell.
Next time, "Mercenary."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.