[ACCELERATOR] Getting Last
Order back and demolishing
that bastard Kihara
was fine and all,
but somehow,
I've ended up involved
with an organization
called GROUP.
We take on the riffraff
that lurk in the dark corners
of Academy City.
Damn.
The only problem is I don't
give a crap about orders.
I'm going to do things
my way no matter what.
[MANAGEMENT]
Come on in!
Most customers these days
have been ordering online
or by email.
I don't get many like you
who drop by in person!
Right now I've got a great deal
on lock-picking sensor breakers.
Cream of the crop, I might add.
These things spell trouble
for money launderers.
So. What might you be
in the market for today?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Nothing.
That's actually not
the reason I'm here.
And since when do we call
Temporary Staffing "Management"?
I'm not your customer.
I'm bringing you in.
[MANAGEMENT]
You bastard! Damn!
He's empty.
[MANAGEMENT yells]
Okay, wait. Just hold on.
I'm not gonna resist.
[gunshot]
[MANAGEMENT grunting]
Stop.
Damn you. I
said I wasn't gonna--
Retrieval.
Contact our subsidiary.
No. No ambulance,
just a transport van.
Now, where's Accelerator?
Not there?
Oh, well.
I'll send Unabara to
Management's base.
Musujime, you keep
providing backup, all right?
Copy that.
Damn.
Looks like our newest
member's run off.
I wonder where he could be.
[FROG-FACED DOCTOR] Back
from Avignon already, I see.
How the hell did you
manage to come up
with that information?
This is a fine how-do-you-do,
don't you think?
Tell me about the electrode.
I want the schematics.
[FROG-FACED DOCTOR]
If your choker isn't working,
I'm happy to fix it for you.
[ACCELERATOR] I have no
intention of letting anyone else
take control of my lifeline.
And that goes for all the
higher-ups, including you, doc.
[FROG-FACED DOCTOR]
I see.
Well, aren't you prepared?
[FROG-FACED DOCTOR] It's my job
to have everything my patients
might need readily available.
By the way, Last Order
was wanting to see you.
If only you could've shown
up a little bit earlier.
[LAST ORDER growls] "It seems
like we're going the wrong way,"
Misaka Misaka protests sternly.
No, miss, we're going
the right way.
"I wanna go to the amusement
park in School District Six,"
says Misaka Misaka,
once again expressing
her fond wishes to him!
[TAXI DRIVER] Right,
and no matter how many times
you repeat yourself,
I'm still not going to do that.
I have strict orders
from your doctor
to take you directly home.
[LAST ORDER groans]
[DRIVER 04A gasps]
[crash]
[MANAGEMENT]
Damn it.
Oh, it's you.
I'm sorry. I know I screwed up.
Could you cut through
these handcuffs, too?
[MANAGEMENT yells]
[UNABARA]
I do still have to wonder,
what sort of jobs was
Management helping with?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
I've been looking into that.
A day or two ago,
he established some kind of
criminal organization.
One that would help fill in
the gaps in terms of manpower.
Apparently, they paid good
money for available muscle
from the outside.
They're gonna make
a move sometime soon.
It's our job to
figure out what it is
and stop it before it happens.
Right. And when
exactly did GROUP
become The Heroes of Justice?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Look.
I need you to collect
any kind of data
that might give us a lead.
Copy.
[UNABARA]
Okay, what do I do now?
I don't get why people are
always too freakin' incompetent
to handle their own damn jobs.
[door opens]
[ACCELERATOR] Wow. This is
where that idiot Unabara
went missing, huh?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Look at this.
It's Aztec magic.
[ACCELERATOR]
Uh...?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Unabara did this.
He has a special
technique that allows him
to transform into other
people by using their skin.
I've never heard anything
like that before.
So he's that guy now?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Yeah.
The people who hit this
place were probably looking
to destroy leads.
I'll bet he's with them now,
waiting for the right moment.
Found something.
I guess you could say
Unabara left us a gift.
If I'm remembering correctly,
Japanese yen issued
by Academy City's mint
have IC chips embedded in them.
[MUSUJIME]
There it is.
It looks like a list of products
belonging to Management.
He did a bit of trading.
With a professional sniper.
His name is Chimitsu Sunazara.
Oh, man. This is actually
a contract for a shooting.
The location is
a concert venue
in School District Seven.
And the target is...
You wanna finish that sentence?
Looks like they're going
after Monaka Oyafune,
a member of the governing board.
She's supposed to be
giving a speech today
on providing voting
rights for students,
since they make up eighty
percent of the population.
According to this,
the speech is about to begin.
Musujime, It's Move Point time.
Hold on. We don't even know
where the sniper's nest--
Stop. You're boring me to death!
[gunshot]
[AUDIENCE yelling]
[ACCELERATOR chuckles]
A little distraction
to break up the event
and now there's no more
sneaky sniper to worry about.
Perfect.
[KAKINE]
Pull out.
Can't. The job's not done yet.
I said pull out.
That means now.
I don't like to repeat
myself, Sunazara.
[ACCELERATOR sighs]
Well that was uneventful.
It's already over?
[phone ringing]
I think I found the name of
the group who hired Sunazara.
"SCHOOL."
I get the sense that they're
smaller scale and informal--
much like us.
Another organization
lurking in the shadows
of Academy City.
It's called SCHOOL?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
There's more to it though.
I'm not sure yet what part
they play in this case, but...
While I was searching,
several names of similar
organizations came up, too.
MEMBER, BLOCK, and ITEM.
[MUGINO]
Huh.
How does today's salmon
lunch taste so much different
from yesterday's
salmon lunch? Bizarre.
[FRENDA]
All told.
I'm getting pretty tired
of canned mackerel.
But not curry, though!
Curry's the best!
[KINUHATA] An ultra-troubled
C-grade movie presented by
the Hong Kong Red
Dragon film company.
Sounds ultra-great.
What do you think, Takitsubo?
Wanna see it?
Incoming signal from
the south-southwest.
So. About that
incident this afternoon.
The one where Monaka
Oyafune almost got shot
while giving a speech?
[HAMAZURA]
Not even gonna say thank you?
Hamazura.
Please send details about
what happened today
to everyone's cell.
[HAMAZURA]
Okay, fine.
[BUNNY GIRL giggles]
[GROUP groans]
Uh, no, wait! Don't look!
Let me resend it!
I accidentally
forwarded something else!
Hamazura.
All told. You really
are a giant creeper.
Bunny girls are an ultra-hit for
you, aren't they, Hamazura?
Hey, that's okay.
I mean, you're who
you're supposed to be,
and I support you in that.
[KINUHATA] Oh, yeah, this is
that thing that SCHOOL bunch
was ultra-planning.
So then... How did they even
manage to go through with it?
I mean, didn't we just get rid
of that sniper three days ago?
Well, they probably
hired a new one.
And I guess that means they also
decided ignoring our warning
was best.
[FRENDA] Oyafune is
on the Governing Board,
but all told,
she's kinda useless.
She has like,
almost zero influence,
so she's not even
worth killing, and yet...
They cared enough
to hire someone new
to carry out the operation.
Now the question is why.
Tell us why, Hamazura!
[HAMAZURA]
Uh...!
Me? Um... Let me think.
Gimme just a moment.
It's right on the
tip of my tongue!
[MUGINO]
Spill it, Hamazura.
All told, the way you get
flustered really grosses me out!
There're so many
levels of "gross,"
it's hard to be specific.
I guess if we're talking about
him, it's like, ultra-gross.
I'm still behind
you all the way.
Even if everyone thinks
you're gross and unfortunate.
I'm still your friend.
Damn! This is so wrong!
I'll have you know,
when I was in Skill Out
I was the leader of
over one hundred men!
Uh-huh.
So what?
Is that it? Get the check.
Um... Where ya' goin'?
We're going to go kill off
all the scumbags of SCHOOL.
[MUGINO]
Let me ask you something.
What do you think
will happen after a VIP
was almost assassinated?
Outside personnel are called in
to cover the
treatment facilities.
They'll round up all the
specialized researchers.
Then materials, machinery,
and anything else they need.
I see.
That could throw security
arrangements off completely.
[MUGINO] That's exactly
what SCHOOL was counting on.
They want to use this
chaos to their advantage.
That's why they targeted
a low-security VIP.
There's our answer.
The Particle Engineering
Laboratory is the only place
that was thrown into disarray
over today's incident.
Which means, that's where
SCHOOL is heading next.
[MUGINO]
Heh.
[MUGINO grunts]
[HAMAZURA]
Whoa. That was incredible!
Mugino's awesome.
She's always full-blast
level five in any setting.
[YOMIKAWA]
Hamazura?
It is you. Thought so.
Surprised to see you out.
I heard you were
taken into custody.
Uh...! Really?
What are you even
doing here, you old hag?
I should be asking
you the same question.
Or is this my answer?
Were you involved
in the incident today?
And what's the story
behind this bus?
Is it stolen?
Of course it's not!
I bought it! With a loan!
Got a license?
I do!
[brakes squeal]
[YOMIKAWA]
Hey, watch where you're going!
That car...
[MUGINO]
Hamazura!
Quit flirting and start driving!
[HAMAZURA]
Ugh. I wasn't flirting!
We have to follow
that black car!
Hurry up!
[YOMIKAWA] Hey! I wasn't
done talking to you!
Shut up.
Everyone's yelling today.
[MUGINO]
Speed up, Hamazura!
[HAMAZURA]
Damn it!
[HAMAZURA] What happened
to Kinuhata and Frenda?
They're fine.
That's not enough to kill them.
So how did things
end up like this?
I mean, you're ranked fourth.
They had a level
five on their side, too.
Teitoku Kakine.
Academy City's number
two son of a bitch.
Hmph. But we still managed
to do some damage.
[HAMAZURA yelling]
What is that?!
Anyway, none of that matters
if we can't catch up to them
and remove the cargo.
We can't let them escape.
Don't worry.
With my AIM Stalker,
I can track anyone.
Once I've been able to log the
bearer's AIM diffusion field,
it doesn't really matter
where they are.
I could even find them
outside the solar system.
All it takes is a simple search
to know their exact location.
[brakes squeal]
[HAMAZURA yells]
[HAMAZURA]
Takitsubo!
[MUGINO]
Let's split up!
We're not gonna fight them?
[MUGINO]
The cargo is what I'm after.
Besides. That girl's power
is pretty obnoxious.
[HAMAZURA]
Uh... uh...!
Um... ugh!
Damn it!
You're after me?
[HAMAZURA yells]
Yeah, what now?
[laughing]
[HAMAZURA yells]
[HAMAZURA coughs]
Well... This is for
all the losers!
[BABY 04A cooing]
--Someone hungry?
--[HAMAZURA yells]
Um... Hi there.
I am a heroine who
has fallen from the sky!
You might want to leave.
This place is dangerous.
[chuckles]
I've lost sight of the target.
Is it possible he's
disguised himself?
Have you ever known him to
transform into a young mother,
a baby, or a stroller?
Die, you idiot.
[KAKINE] Laying all of this
groundwork was a real pain.
But I have the nanoparticle
object interference
adsorption manipulator
to show for it.
Better known as "the tweezers."
This breakthrough will
lead me to Aleister.
Kakine!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It appears
that someone has hacked into
the fifth School District
Computer Virus Archive Center.
In addition to storing
many unanalyzed viruses,
they also house multiple
experimental ones,
deliberately created by Academy
City's research institutes.
Those would be bad enough here,
but if they made it outside--
Well, their infrastructure
will collapse.
So we're clear,
just how far
outside is "outside?"
Huh. Know what I heard
about Academy City security?
That their safeguarding
priorities are inside-outward,
not outside-inward as
some might be assuming.
If so, then they should be more
than well-equipped for this.
An externally-connected
terminal?
[DRIVER 04B]
Commencing emergency shutdown
of externally-connected
terminals.
Third School District north
terminal is shut down.
Second School District
south terminal is shut down.
What is it?
[DRIVER 04B] The Thirteenth
School District's west terminal
isn't responding.
I can't confirm a shutdown.
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
Could their schemes
be any more transparent?
You're right, I'd say
odds are pretty good
they're trying to lure us there.
I don't know who these guys are,
but it seems like they're
begging for a fight
they won't win.
[DRIVER 04B] What should
we do about Monaka Oyafune's
attempted assassination?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
We'll come back to that later.
[DRIVER 04B] All right,
what about Mr. Unabara?
I was never really
planning to rescue him.
[phone ringing]
[YAMATE (UNABARA)]
It's Unabara.
Who are you out goofing
around with now? SCHOOL?
Well, no. It's BLOCK.
I'm sure you've figured it out,
but BLOCK's hacking satellites.
It's not SCHOOL.
However, it's a diversion.
What they're really after
is the aerospace engineering
research institute's auxiliary
satellite control center.
I'll let you deal with that.
Talk to you later.
They want the
satellite control center.
Makes sense.
I can see why.
The Hikoboshi II satellite
is fully equipped
with a high-caliber
surface-attack laser.
But that doesn't mean
we disregard the virus leak
at the storage center.
[pounding noise]
You guys have fun
with those jerks.
Playing decoy games
isn't my thing.
[laughing]
[CITIZEN 04A yells]
Uh... Who are you?
Take me to the
satellite control center.
[CITIZEN 04A]
Yes, sir.
[KAMIJO] Those struggling
to escape control.
Those who voluntarily
leap into the framework.
Their motives cross,
provoking a new battle.
Next time, "Dark Matter."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.