[STIYL] Well, now, Biagio
Buzoni and Ms. Lorenzetti.
I suppose you already
know what we're going
to ask you about.
If you want a lesson from
the Church on the Bible,
you can bring any questions
you have to us on Sunday.
Just like everyone else.
[STIYL]
The tough act is pointless.
If necessary, we will use
whatever means we have
to extract the information
needed from inside your skulls.
Don't take Necessarius lightly.
[BIAGIO]
Hmm...?
Now, the Right Seat of God.
Tell us what you know.
If we do as you ask,
then I expect
you'll be willing to answer
some questions for us.
I want to know what
exactly is going on
outside these walls.
I'm sure you can
guess, can't you?
It's either what you're
thinking, or it's much worse.
"San Pietro, slips through
the evil clutches
of the emperor and sorcerer."
Oh, no!
Lidvia!
Are you ready to talk?
First, Oriana Thompson.
I request that you release her.
Allow the opportunity
to lead others
who have been caught up
in this unrest safely out of it
as is her will.
So that's it?
Even in your current
situation here,
you are still seeking
out relief for the weak.
Do you really feel
you're in any position
to make demands?
She can't be let go,
and wouldn't want to be.
She's in a temporary partnership
with the English Puritan Church.
The union has
a condition, and that is
for her leader to
protect the weak.
And aren't you her leader?
Even if you order
her to be released,
Oriana herself would
never agree to it.
You don't want her resolve
to be for nothing, do you?
If the unrest has been
created by the Roman Orthodoxy,
or rather,
the Right Seat of God,
then it would seem that
the key to resolving it
lies is in the act of
bringing them down.
Don't you agree?
[LIDVIA] Then tell me, what
is it that you want from us?
I believe our objective's
been made clear.
We wish to rescue the lost sheep
who have been swallowed
up by the overwhelming
power of magic.
That's our goal now,
as it has always been.
I've never had the opportunity
to meet any of them personally,
and I have only heard bits
and pieces of information
about them on occasion.
From that, I can say...
The Right Seat of God is...
[KAMIJO yelling]
[KAMIJO grunting]
Can't breathe... Strangled...
[CITIZEN 02A gasps]
[KAMIJO coughing]
[ITSUWA]
Um... Are you okay?
[KAMIJO]
Yeah. Great.
Hey, you're with the Amakusa.
Itsuwa, right?
Yeah. That's me.
It's been a long time.
Yeah. Did Tsuchimikado
ask you to come here?
Where did he go?
Huh?
[KAMIJO] We're tracking
down the Document of C.
Supposedly it's being
used to instigate
the demonstrations that
have been popping up.
What?! How do you
know about that?
Who told you?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Listen close, Kami.
I'm gonna tell you all
about this Document of C.
Originally, it was sort
of like a deed, y'know?
Something that shows
who controls what land.
It said the land rights to
territories formerly ruled
by Constantine had been
given over to the Roman pope.
A fun fact...
When you read the Document
of C, its seal emerges.
Which is said to be
proof that the land
belongs to the Papacy.
Make sense?
Good. Now, when we're talking
about it as a magical item,
it's got even crazier powers.
Check this out.
Everything that the
Roman pope declares
instantly becomes
"accurate information"--
it's seen as a fact
no matter what it is.
Insane, right?
So if the pope
declares something,
even if there's no basis for it,
for followers of Roman Orthodoxy
that declaration ends
up being correct.
'Kay. So what's the catch?
I was just about to get to that.
There is a catch.
And it's a pretty important one.
It has to be set up
in the Vatican
for it to work at all.
Also, it's not like it
alters the laws of physics
or anything.
It can only make people
believe what's said.
[KAMIJO] And that's
everything I was told.
The document is still
within the church.
They're trying to use
it against Academy City.
In an effort to make
everyone believe
we're the bad guys.
And that's what's causing
the demonstrations?
Possibly.
I assumed someone would've
let you guys know about it.
No.
We received a request from
the English Puritan Church.
To survey the magical
value of the geoducts here.
All over France,
that's what I was doing.
Before you fell out of the sky.
[KAMIJO]
France?
[ITSUWA]
Yes.
We're in the city
of Avignon right now,
in southern France.
Huh.
But if the Document of C
can only be used
in the Vatican, then...
[ITSUWA]
Um...
Sorry to interrupt, but do
you mind if I go get my bag?
I just remembered that I left
it up on the bridge earlier.
[KAMIJO]
Hold on.
You jumped from
there to save me?
[ITSUWA]
I didn't think it all through.
Well, good thing.
Because if you had,
I probably wouldn't be here.
So thank you.
Oh, it wasn't
that big of a deal.
[KAMIJO gasps]
Hey, so, do you happen
to have a change of clothes
in that bag?
[ITSUWA] Yeah. Just in
case I need a disguise.
[KAMIJO 'Kay, good,
you might wanna grab it.
[ITSUWA gasps]
I... I'm so sorry you
had to see me like this.
How embarrassing!
[laughing]
I'd feel less anxious
if she were to at least
freak out or something.
[KAMIJO]
It doesn't seem to be broken.
[ITSUWA]
I'm back. Thanks for waiting.
[gasps]
[KAMIJO]
Uh... Itsuwa?
What? This was just supposed
to be a quick disguise
to throw over my tank
top in emergencies,
and it's all I had!
Please don't say anything else!
I'm already embarrassed enough.
[KAMIJO] Well, Kanzaki
wears stuff like that, so...
How dare you!
The priestess would never
wear something this shameful!
Oh. My bad.
Anyway, the Amakusa
Church is actually looking
for the Document of C, too.
So maybe we could
hang out together
until you meet up
with Tsuchimikado?
[KAMIJO] Actually, I'd
appreciate the company.
I mean, if you're sure.
Yes!
[KAMIJO] We have big-name
shops like these in Japan, too.
Aren't there any that're
more well-established
and out of the way?
Yeah, but we'd stick out
like sore thumbs there.
That's the issue?
Come on, let's go inside.
Okay, let me message
Tsuchimikado real quick.
--Think he's from Academy City?
--[CITIZEN 02C] You see that?
[KAMIJO]
Were they demonstrators?
[ITSUWA]
Uh-huh.
[KAMIJO] So, why Avignon
and not the Vatican?
[ITSUWA] Are you familiar
with an incident that happened
in the late thirteenth century,
known as the Avignon Papacy?
[ITSUWA] There was a
dispute between France
and the Roman Orthodoxy,
and when the king of France won,
he decided to incarcerate
the Roman pope
here in Avignon.
And then, for the next
sixty-eight years,
the functions of the
Holy Roman See
were moved to the
Papal Palace in Avignon.
[ITSUWA]
However...
[KAMIJO gasps]
Oh! Just a moment, please.
I think I have a wipe.
Thank you.
No wait, I mean... Uh, merci?
I'm sorry. Please finish
what you were saying.
What's wrong?
[ITSUWA]
Oh. Nothing.
I'm fine, really.
Hey.
Can the pope's work
be done anywhere?
Or is it something that
specifically has to be done
at the Vatican?
It depends.
There are plenty of things
he wouldn't be able
to do away from home.
Like, say, for example,
using magical items.
Specifically, those that
are within the Papal domain.
The Church's solution
was to establish
an enchanted pipeline using
geoducts between the Vatican
and Avignon, making it
possible to control
the facilities within
the Papal domain remotely.
So you're saying...
They'll be able to
use the magical items
here in Avignon now?
[ITSUWA]
Exactly.
But why?
Seems like a
roundabout way to go.
Wouldn't it be easier to just
use them in the Vatican?
[ITSUWA] Well... there are
some particular arrangements
that are required in
order to use them there.
Doing it this way,
he can ignore or abridge
some of those and use
the items at his discretion.
But the trade-off is that it
seems to take a long time
to activate the pipeline.
So we may still
be able to stop them
from using the Document of C.
May still be able to? Huh.
[ITSUWA] I'm sorry!
This is all just guesswork!
No, it's fine.
Is there anything
I can do to hel--?!
[MOB 02A]
Look! There's one!
--[MOB 02B] Where?
--[MOB 02A] Grab him!
[glass breaks]
[WAITRESS 02A] I'm gonna
have to ask you to leave now!
There's a guy from Academy
City hiding in here!
[PATRON 02C]
Academy City?
[PATRON 02D]
Who, him?
[ITSUWA]
This way!
[MOB 02A]
Don't just stand there, get him!
Wait! That little boy!
He's fine.
No one's gonna get
killed out there!
Come on! Hurry!
[MOB yelling]
[KAMIJO]
Damn it!
It's not their fault!
Those caught in the middle
are the ones who suffer most!
I have to put
an end to this,
and I've gotta do it quickly.
[KAMIJO]
Hey, Itsuwa.
I don't suppose you've
ever been caught up
in one of these riots before.
Well, no.
If I sensed it coming,
I'd be sure to stay far away.
Yeah, I figured.
The timing is way
too convenient.
I'm gonna guess
that all this violence
is an ambush planned
by the enemy.
[ITSUWA]
You think so?
It doesn't look like we'll
have time for Tsuchimikado
to contact us.
That means...
We'll have to head to the
Papal Palace on our own.
If they return to the Vatican,
those jerks can still
use the Document of C.
We need to stop this thing
here while we have the chance.
Make sure to keep your head down
when we charge through there.
Right. Let's go.
[LIDVIA] The Right Seat of God
is said to be an organization
devoted to overcoming
original sin.
The sin committed
by Adam and Eve
when they ate from
the tree of knowledge.
The story says
that their children,
all of mankind,
are born with this same sin.
Correct. However, there is
an exception to that story.
[STIYL]
The Holy Mother Mary.
Immaculate Conception.
It's said that the sin
was removed from her
because she would
bear the Son of God.
[LIDVIA]
And what this shows us is that,
even though we are taught
to believe the only way
to wash away original
sin is by having
a firm faith in the Son of God,
there is a loophole.
Are you saying they've
obtained the means to do so?
[LIDVIA]
Yes, at least partially.
Word is, the Right Seat
of God has successfully
diluted their sins
as much as possible.
And though it is not complete,
with their sin removed,
it is said they'll be able
to use the techniques
of angels and of the Lord,
which are usually
unavailable to humanity.
If what you say is true,
their essence would no
longer be strictly human,
but rather closer
to that of the angels.
Which would mean
that the ultimate goal
of the Right Seat of God
is to rid themselves
of what little original sin
remains within them.
[LIDVIA]
That is one of the avenues
that is open to them, however,
their true objective
is much grander
and has always been
broadly laid out.
And what's that?
The literal meaning
of their group's name.
They aspire to reach
the Right Seat of God.
[MOB yelling]
[KAMIJO] It would have
to be like this, wouldn't it?
[ITSUWA]
Yes.
The Papal Palace is on
the other side of that crowd.
We'll have to push through.
All right.
Well, then, let's get moving.
[phone rings]
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Hey, Kami!
You made it okay?
Tsuchimikado, where
the hell are you?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Me? I'm on
my way to the Papal Palace.
I knew it.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
How?
I don't remember ever explaining
that part of it to you.
Itsuwa from the Amakusa told me.
We're trying to get there
but the rioting is too severe.
Is this also because of
the Document of C's power?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Bingo! Well deduced, my friend!
Which means you
can wait if you want,
but the situation won't improve.
Isn't there anything
else we can do?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Sure!
Here's a question.
Do you know why the
Papal Palace of Avignon
is viewed as so important?
Because it allows them
to control facilities
in the Vatican?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Bingo!
That's it! The geoduct pipeline!
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Double bingo!
If we could manage
to sever the geoduct
that connects Avignon
with the Vatican...
Right! Even if it's too hard for
us to reach the Papal Palace,
maybe we can at least
get close enough
to the pipeline on the way.
And then all I have to do is
wreck it with my right hand.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Yeah, I'm
gonna suggest avoiding that.
But geoducts are magic,
and my hand destroys magic.
So why--
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Thing is...
It's hard to identify what
exactly that hand of yours does.
Sure, it's supposed to cancel
out supernatural powers
and what-not, but...
What if there are exceptions?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Itsuwa, was it?
What do you know about
demolishing pipelines?
Uh, lots!
If the Amakusa way of
doing things will work.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Sure, why not?
Then I'll leave the
hunt for the pipeline
in your capable hands.
I gotta make my move now.
Later!
[KAMIJO]
This is a museum?
Yes, but I'm guessing
all the rioting
must've spooked them
into closing early.
It'd be great if we
could poke around.
But how?
We gotta make this fast.
Okay...
Hey!
[ITSUWA]
Looks like this is the place!
This power resembles
Roman Orthodox style.
And this duct is for Western
church-of-the-cross societies.
[KAMIJO] It doesn't look
like anything to me.
It's fairly cleverly concealed,
so it's difficult to do.
Let's get moving before the
enemy realizes we're here.
Is that a hairdryer?
Do the Amakusa
use household items
to build their spells?
[ITSUWA] Yes. The Pamphlet,
mineral water, and white--
[gasps]
[KAMIJO]
What's the matter?
[ITSUWA]
I'm so sorry.
I know it's awkward,
but they're required
for the framework of the spell.
[KAMIJO chuckles]
[ITSUWA] It's impossible to
destroy the geoduct completely.
But I can at least make
the pipeline unusable.
[ITSUWA]
Here we go.
Get out of the way!
Itsuwa!
No, don't! Stay back!
[ITSUWA]
Get outside! Quickly!
[TERRA]
Well, well.
I suppose accuracy
really does drop
when something's launched
from greater distances.
That's magic.
Roman Orthodox?
[TERRA]
I'm not saying you're wrong,
but if you must assign a label,
I would prefer that
you address me
as the Right Seat of God.
My name is Terra of the Left.
Nice to meet you.
It looks like my time
has finally arrived.
It's been difficult.
See, we do not have
the ability to use
the common sort of magic
that humans prefer.
And enacting the Document of C
must be left to
other spellcasters.
So I hope you'll consider
spending a little time
with me today.
I've been so bored lately.
I could use some entertainment.
--[KAMIJO grunts]
--[ITSUWA gasps]
That was some powerful force,
but with my right hand...
Well that was a twist.
Ordinarily that attack
would have killed you.
So that's Imagine Breaker,
right? How fun.
I heard that you tormented
Vento of the Front.
You ready?
[KAMIJO yelling]
I apologize for what comes next.
[ITSUWA]
Seven Teachings!
Seven Blades!
Precedence.
[laughs]
[TERRA] Precedence. Outer wall
lower, physical body higher.
lower, blade motion higher!
[KAMIJO]
Move!
[ITSUWA grunts]
[KAMIJO grunts]
I'd heard many a tale of the
Imagine Breaker beforehand,
so I admit, I did have some
expectations coming into this.
But honestly, I'm disappointed.
You must've caught
Vento on a bad day.
Because I can't see how anybody
would have
trouble defeating you.
[KAMIJO]
He's powerful.
So this is the
Right Seat of God.
[KAMIJO]
Unrest breeds more unrest,
and the city is enveloped
in the flames of science.
What secret will Terra
reveal about my right hand?
Next time, "The Document of C."
When Science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.