[TÉCPATL] Since you're part of
this dark outfit called GROUP,
the usual intelligence
networks weren't able
to pin down your location.
We ended up using Shiokishi
here at the core
of Academy City instead.
Here's the plan.
We're going to end your life.
Wait, is that...? [grunts]
Yes. It's the original
text of the grimoire.
[UNABARA grunts, yells]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[TÉCPATL] Normally, that kind of
blast would have directly struck
celestial bodies.
Apparently, the rabbit
bones used to fuel it
were of poor quality.
What the hell did you just do?
And what have you
done to Tochtli?
Rabbit bones, remember?
Perhaps it might make more
sense if I drew you a picture.
[laughs]
You have to admit
it's entertaining.
I bet she's lost at
least half her bones.
What is wrong with you?
Técpatl!
Nice one.
See, this is the way
all our fights should be.
Let's expand our knowledge
in seizing Aztec control.
[HAMAZURA]
K-K-Kinuhata!
If you don't mind, I think
I'll go ahead and kill you now.
Be my guest.
I'm not petty enough to
take offense at the drivel
of other people, so good luck.
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
[laughs]
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[SUGITANI] I happen to know
that Amata Kihara was able
to break through
your Reflection Barrier
by pulling his punch
before impact.
Also...
Teitoku Kakine knew
to utilize matter
that doesn't exist in our world.
[crack]
I see.
I'd love to take a page from
their exceptional methods
and duplicate them,
but I cannot.
We call that a third-stringer.
Even though you've got
modest skills of your own,
all you know how to do is
follow that old man's orders.
A dude like you
claims to be the heir
of those who fought
in the name of justice.
You saying that bastard
Shiokishi seems like
a good guy to you?
And now, for some reason,
you think you're in the
right for following him?
Are you trying to make me laugh?
It's true, the word "good"
always ends up
being exploited by those
in power somehow.
Although, if your default is
to relegate everything to evil,
is that really going
to solve every last one
of the world's problems?
From my perspective,
the only thing
your brand of evil does
is scavenge the scraps that drop
down from the table of good.
You scumbag, the moment
you call any good deed
"table scraps" makes it
obvious nothing good you do
is genuine.
You're telling me
I'm not genuine?
As if you know someone
good who is?
Damn right I do.
So good that it pisses me off
how you caused me to remember.
[SUGITANI]
I see.
And it is quite unfortunate that
you will never see them again.
Because you're about
to die right here.
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
By the way, your electrode
has been modified
so that it can easily be
controlled remotely when needed.
Once you are isolated
from the Misaka Network,
your fighting strength
drops to zero.
This is the "good"
I've been talking about.
I'm amazed by the
amount of struggle a man
must endure just to be good
in a world full of miscreants.
[STEPHANIE grunts]
What happened?
[KINUHATA] Let's see, you were
ultra-familiar with fighting
against espers,
and you had the ability
to determine our weaknesses.
On the other hand,
you didn't seem to understand
that I am also a person
who has had to fight
ultra-hard to stay alive.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I am virtually unbeatable
in close-quarters combat.
So the most dangerous
thing I could ultra-face
is taking an ultra-precise
attack from someplace
out of my reach.
But with the way you
choose to fire at random,
Sunazara proved to be a much
deadlier shot than you are.
[STEPHANIE gasps]
[STEPHANIE] Is that
supplementary liquid nitrogen?
[UNABARA grunts]
[UNABARA] The original text
is streaming inside my head.
It may destroy me,
but I must defeat this guy.
[UNABARA grunts]
Goodness.
You see, it really does require
some experience, Etzali.
If you're going to use
this as a weapon,
then you need to take
the necessary steps
to prevent the
backflow of knowledge.
[UNABARA] So then,
you haven't actually read
the original text,
have you?
[TÉCPATL grunts]
[coughs]
What just happened?
You don't know, do you?
Allow me to enlighten you.
The original grimoires
favor those who can best
spread their knowledge.
[TÉCPATL] You transcribed
the stone tablet?
[UNABARA] You've never
come face to face
with the original
text's knowledge.
So what made you think
that it would ever let you
get away with that?
[SUGITANI grunts]
But how?
Well, since you asked,
I'll explain.
This is a jamming device.
It's a what?
Just a simple electronic jammer.
It has the ability to affect
the Misaka Network.
I analyzed the EM
waves from before
and then calculated
their inverse.
See, this is how
evil's supposed to work.
I also could not name
a single difference
between you and me.
The last word anyone would
ever use to describe me
is "good."
You and I use the same methods,
and that makes you
a prize-winning villain.
[KINUHATA] I think you
kinda overdid it, there.
I can see how you ultra-got
the gun on your own,
but how did you get a
six-winger attack helicopter?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
If I could get an
attack helicopter,
the obvious move would've
been to attack you
from well beyond your range.
Think about it.
[KINUHATA]
True.
Then who was it?
Is there someone else around
who's ultra-out to get us?
No way!
[KINUHATA]
Run, Hamazura!
Ultra-get out of here!
I'm pretty sure you're
the one they're after!
What's that?
Come on! You heard her!
Wait! What about Kinuhata?
Just hurry!
Damn it!
[KINUHATA grunts]
Ultra-what is it you
think you're doing?
[HEART MEASURE] Were you
aware that Aleister is devising
and carrying out a very
important plan of some sort?
That's right. As it happens,
Toma Kamijo and Accelerator
are two of the irregular
factors that fall within
the tolerance levels
of this plan.
That's why they can be
situated at the center
and be used as much as
needed to make it succeed.
On the other hand, it's not the
same for your friend Hamazura.
He appears to be a bit
of a hindrance.
He was supposed
to have been killed
during the conflict among
our dark subgroups.
Shiage Hamazura is a
Level Zero without any power.
He has no definite role to play,
so he's trying to achieve
something all on his own--
perhaps he seeks
a new kind of value.
Not even Aleister
knows what to expect.
But depending on
what it turns out to be,
it may or may not have
the potential to damage
Aleister's plan.
Therefore, Academy City
is marshalling
all of its forces
to kill Hamazura
before he causes
any destruction.
What do you think?
Is he worth the trouble?
[SHIOKISHI]
DRAGON? [grunts]
I'm sure you all have
your own suppositions.
Oh, come on, you're not
gonna try and tell us
you know nothing
about it, are you?
Believe me, it would be
easier to say I didn't.
But unfortunately, I did
learn a few things.
It's something nobody
should ever be forced
to lay their eyes upon.
We get that.
Just tell us what it is.
Where is DRAGON,
and what is it exactly?
You don't get it, do you?
DRAGON can be found everywhere.
Look.
Turn around and you'll see
DRAGON behind you now.
What? Hey!
[thud]
[VOICE]
DRAGON?
The name isn't exactly wrong,
but to be the most accurate,
"Angel" would also apply.
However, if you want
to be more precise
when addressing me directly,
it would be prudent
to use the following
name instead.
The name that
belongs to the being
who once gave an eccentric
sorcerer, Aleister Crowley,
the necessary knowledge
in the necessary amount.
"Aiwass."
[HAMAZURA, TAKITSUBO panting]
Hold on!
Run.
Hamazura, please.
It's the only way now.
[HAMAZURA]
Huh?
[TAKITSUBO] If we continue
like this, we'll both be caught,
so just go.
[TAKITSUBO]
Hamazura.
[HAMAZURA]
Be quiet.
Someone's coming.
I hear something.
[gasps]
Everything will be fine.
Please go.
At least this way I can
buy you some time.
You can't be serious!
[rumbling]
[HAMAZURA]
Please, somebody please find us.
Some kind of hero.
Just show up out of
nowhere and save her life.
Please!
Hey, looks like we made it!
I have no idea who
stepped in to help us,
but we survived this!
[laughing]
[MUGINO]
Hamazura.
[footsteps]
It can't be...
[MUGINO] Don't you dare let
these two-bit bastards
come in here and take your life.
That would be so unfair,
don't you think?
Besides, I've already decided
that I deserve the honor
of tearing you limb from limb!
[AIWASS]
Why do you look so mystified?
I don't believe my
sudden appearance
could really be that
incomprehensible to you.
It would help if you
tell me what you are
and why the hell you
would wrap yourself up
in a codename like "DRAGON."
[AIWASS] This is where I'm
going to have to attempt
an explanation, isn't it?
My identity is not
that big of a deal.
I'm an insignificant being
and nothing more.
Huh?
[AIWASS]
Oh, dear.
It appears I'm not able to
express that great a degree
of meaning in this world.
Are you perhaps
familiar with the phrase
"Fuse= KAZAKIRI?"
[ACCELERATOR]
Huh?
[AIWASS sighs]
Well, it is a being that is
known as an artificial angel.
A mass of AIM dispersion fields.
It is also something
of a production line
used to give me
this form as Aiwass.
Just appearing for the
fun of it is fine and all,
but now what do I do?
What would you like to do?
Would you like to upset
Aleister's aspirations
based on the information
only I can give you?
Why do I feel like you're
just jerking my chain?
[AIWASS]
I don't know.
I will not be the
one who is upset
if Aleister's plan is derailed.
Whether it takes
ten thousand years,
or even one hundred thousand.
I'll just wait for another
opportunity to manifest.
Pardon me, "emerge."
Oh, and just so you know.
The plan that Aleister
is undertaking?
It's already starting
to come apart.
Meaning...?
[AIWASS] Meaning the fractures
are slowly starting to widen.
And if it keeps up,
the keystone of his plan,
Last Order, is certain to
disintegrate sooner or later.
[ACCELERATOR]
How dare you!
I don't care if you are a
mass of AIM dispersion fields
or some kind of dragon-angel
or whatever.
If you maliciously intend
to do harm to that kid,
I promise I will
show you no mercy!
[coughing, grunting]
[AIWASS]
Oh, no.
That was my mistake, I'm afraid.
Aleister, you messed with that
structural virus, didn't you?
What a pity.
Goodness, I'm so sorry.
If you want to kill me,
you will first have to deal
with these glowing wings
before you have
a hope of success.
[ACCELERATOR] I'll kill you,
you son of a bitch!
[AIWASS] Let's see,
"Do what thou wilt,
shall be the whole
of the Law."
Is that right?
[ACCELERATOR yells]
[AIWASS]
Is that all you have left?
I tried to draw you out
by explicitly mentioning
Last Order, but alas.
[ACCELERATOR]
I get it now.
What was it you said?
You appear by using
AIM diffusion fields,
isn't that right?
And the only way you
were able to control them
is by having that kid become
infected with the virus
so you could create
that Fuse=KAZAKIRI crap.
I'm right, aren't I?
Then if that's the case...
[AIWASS]
Now you're using your head.
Looks like you've also
reset it to work on
the entire Misaka Network.
But do you realize
that in doing so,
you've also managed to
personally cut the lifeline
responsible for
keeping yourself alive.
Hey! I'm done with you!
[AIWASS]
I see.
Then why don't you
go ahead and show me...
...thy "Law."
[HAMAZURA pants, yells]
How the hell is
she still alive?!
[MUGINO]
Hamazura!
You still make as
quick an escape as ever,
but are you sure you should?
What will happen to
your beloved Takitsubo?
[TAKITSUBO grunts]
[HAMAZURA gasps]
[MUGINO laughs]
Ooh! What part should
I burn first?
Aw. I'd love to see
this precious face sizzle.
[TAKITSUBO gasps]
[MUGINO] Why are you trying
to play the tragic heroine?
I thought you were supposed to
be a simple, helpless princess.
What's wrong?
Now all of a sudden you don't
have the strength to fight?
If you're too afraid to
take the ability crystal,
you can run.
But be aware that Hamazura
will be charred to death
if you do!
Feel free to leave
him here to die!
Yes! That's it! Do it!
Hurry up and swallow your
ace-in-the-hole crystal!
[TAKITSUBO]
Hamazura...
[HAMAZURA]
Mugino!
[TAKITSUBO grunting]
[MUGINO laughs]
What was that supposed
to be, Hamazura?
I'm so confused--who was it
that you were trying to protect?
Hey, if you prefer to finish
her off yourself, be my guest!
[HAMAZURA]
This is getting old.
But it looks like killing
you only once wasn't enough
to get you out of my life.
No! Of course it wasn't
enough, you idiot!
Once is never
enough for anything!
Come back!
Are you mocking me now?
Smoke screen?
Think you're a ninja? [grunts]
[MUGINO gasps]
Wow. I did it.
I got her!
[laughs]
[MUGINO]
Hamazura.
[MUGINO] How could you
ever think some common
mass-produced weapons would
be anywhere near enough
to take down the
fourth-ranked Meltdowner?
Come on, Hamazura.
[HAMAZURA yells]
[HAMAZURA grunts]
[HAMAZURA] This looks like
an endurance testing room
for air racing.
Honestly, this is
getting ridiculous.
Neither Teitoku Kakine nor
I have been allowed to die.
It seems like the chairman
of the governing board
just wants to use us for
our Level Five abilities.
He wants it so badly,
he did all this to our bodies.
Tell me the truth, Hamazura.
How was it possible for me
to become this hideous
of a monster?
[HAMAZURA]
Mugino.
That's what you want
me to say, isn't it?
Tell me the truth!
[MUGINO laughs]
Why are you shaking
like a little leaf?
I know, while you're at it,
why don't you give me
one of those strange,
hilarious screams?
I'm going to coat you in
melted iron and let it cool,
and then turn you into a weird,
yet fascinating work of art!
[MUGINO]
Huh?
[ANNOUNCEMENT 17A]
This is a warning.
Experiment commencing.
What did you do, Hamazura?
Does that mean it's over?
[AIWASS] That Aleister is
such a worrywart.
He was taking more
precautions than usual.
He put up several robust
barriers against me
that I didn't know about.
So? Damn you.
[AIWASS] I hate to do this to
you after you've already put
so much effort into your fight.
But as it turns out...
I have the ability
to change form.
Hamazura! You're alive!
[crying]
[phone buzzes]
[KINUHATA]
Hamazura, listen to me.
Get ultra-away from there
right this instant!
[HAMAZURA]
Kinuhata?
[KINUHATA] There's a detached
force from Academy City
on its way.
Take Takitsubo and ultra-run
as fast as you can!
Okay, but where are
we supposed to run to?
[AIWASS]
Aleister, Tell the truth.
You wouldn't happen to
admire them, would you?
Those who follow the feelings
that spring up within them
without being
encouraged by anyone?
Those who keep moving forward?
Those who have committed
great mistakes in the past,
and even while struggling
with these sins,
continue to move
with good intentions?
Do you envy those who,
without being chosen,
and without being qualified,
can miraculously become a hero?
If only for the sake
of someone they love.
Each of these are people
who may get beaten down
quite often, but they
always search for a way
to get back up on their feet.
They seem to be well-equipped
with something you do not have.
It appears that in
your time of struggle,
all you could manage to do
was crumble and lament.
As such, it is only natural
for you to wish you were
more like them.
[ALEISTER] Aiwass, I will
make use of anything I can
to survive.
Even if that manifests
in my using you.
Allow me to say
something to you as well.
Indeed, you have an advantage,
but there are no guarantees
that your advantage is absolute,
or that it will last forever.
[AIWASS]
The girl is a different matter.
She will most certainly
perish at some point.
If you don't want
to mourn her later,
you should proceed down
a path other than the one
you are currently on.
Go to Russia.
Specifically, the Elizalina
Alliance of Independent Nations.
Remember the term "Index
Librorum Prohibitorum."
There will be an important
item pertaining to it.
--[ACCELERATOR gasps]
--[crash]
[ACCELERATOR]
Russia.
Is something wrong, or...?
No, I'm fine, really.
Please don't ever leave me.
You have my word.
Like I would leave you.
Damn it!
I'm never gonna
leave you, all right?
[KAMIJO]
Just you wait.
Academy City and Russia.
Everything becomes
embroiled and it begins.
As for what,
that much is obvious.
World War III.
Next time, "The Alliance
of Independent Nations."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.