[MUGINO yawns]
Man. Come on. He's so slow.
Hamazura?
Yeah. I sent him out on a
garbage run a while ago.
And he's supposed to
pick up a salmon lunch
after he's done with that.
It's about time.
What took you so long? Huh?
[KAKINE]
Ah, so this is where you are.
Well, if it isn't Dark Matter.
I really wish you
would use my name.
If you've forgotten,
I'll refresh your memory.
It's Teitoku Kakine.
And I thought I'd stop
by to declare victory.
[HAMAZURA]
I don't know who you are, but...
I'm sorry that I'm the
one sending you off.
[HAMAZURA]
In this city,
those without power
are like trash.
Nobody even bothers
to help them.
And I'm sure I'm one of them.
[phone buzzing]
[HAMAZURA]
Kinuhata?
I was just finishing the job.
[KINUHATA]
Hamazura, secure us a vehicle
as fast as you can, please.
[HAMAZURA]
Huh?
We're currently under
fire from SCHOOL.
[HAMAZURA]
What?
It appears that one of
their targets is Takitsubo.
I bet they're here because they
heard about her AIM Stalker.
They wanna get rid of her.
As long as she stays safe,
we can still turn this around.
So, I need you to get
her somewhere safe as--
Kinuhata!
I'm ultra-fine.
[TAKITSUBO]
I'm fighting with you.
That's okay.
You just stay put.
There you are!
[gasps]
[KAKINE]
Huh? What is this?
Oh, that was awesome.
Guess they were snuffed.
Tough break for Sunazara
and his sniper rifle, huh?
[KINUHATA] Which means
you're gonna have to face me!
Do you really think
you can beat me
with Level Four Offense Armor?
I'm well beyond the level you're
able to scheme your way out of.
[HAMAZURA] Either I go up
there and get killed,
or I bail and wind up
in the incinerator.
[yelps]
Damn it!
[HAMAZURA]
Kinuhata?
Huh?
Let her go right now!
Who the hell are you?
Don't tell me you're expecting
to defeat me with that toy.
Oh, so you're a
sacrificial pawn.
Your big boss Mugino
has already left.
Of course. Damn that woman!
[TAKITSUBO]
No, don't.
Just go. Please, Hamazura.
I'm Level Four. You're Zero.
It's okay. I promise
I'll protect you.
Takitsubo.
What is that?
What the--?
Are you trying to disrupt
my AIM diffusion field?
You wanna take
over my ability?
Hurry up, Hamazura!
[gunshot]
[KAKINE] I don't recall
ever asking for help.
[GIRL IN DRESS]
Hello. Long time, no see.
[HAMAZURA]
What? You again?
[GIRL IN DRESS]
Hm? So that's what happened.
Yeah.
She must be really desperate
to use an Ability Crystal.
I don't even know what that is.
It's a chemical that triggers
an adverse reaction.
She was using it to make her
ability run out of control.
In most cases though, it does
nothing but harm to the user.
And even if it does
produce favorable results,
one shouldn't keep using it.
[cries]
Takitsubo!
She just has to use her
power one or two more times
and she'll destroy herself.
That's fine by me. She can
finish the job for us.
[GIRL IN DRESS]
Heart Measure.
What that does is shrink
the emotional distance
between you and me.
The closeness we feel now is...
I dunno, that of old friends?
You wouldn't shoot your
friend, would you?
[HAMAZURA]
Applied telepathy?
[gasps]
[yells]
Damn it!
Takitsubo!
[phone buzzing]
[HAMAZURA]
Mugino.
[MUGINO] Hamazura,
I'm looking for Takitsubo.
Is she with you?
Damn it, Mugino!
You're just gonna run
away by yourself?
[MUGINO] Do me a favor
and pipe down, all right?
Our counterattack begins
now, so be ready.
We'll take this chance
and use Takitsubo's power
to pursue SCHOOL.
[HAMAZURA]
That's crazy!
You're gonna get
everyone killed!
Besides, she's in
no shape for that!
So she's still alive, then?
Well, thank goodness!
Because I am going to need her
to produce some serious results
even if it kills her.
Now then.
[gasps]
Just go, Hamazura.
I don't want to get
you killed. Go.
[gasps]
[KAMIJO] Will you accept
no responsibility?
You ever try asking for help?
Or just lashing out?
The reason people
look down on you
has nothing to do with power,
or your lack of it.
That's just an illusion
you're clinging to.
At some point, you'll
need to let it go.
How about right now?
[HAMAZURA]
Yeah, an illusion.
I get it now.
He was right, damn it!
[YOMIKAWA]
Really, Hamazura?
You do know what I do
for a living, right?
I know it looks bad. I'll
explain everything afterwards!
I just need you to take
her somewhere safe
as fast as possible!
She could fall apart
at any moment
because of something called
an Ability Crystal.
[YOMIKAWA]
Excuse me?!
What did you say?
Because I thought you
said "Ability Crystal."
[HAMAZURA]
I did! That's the reason she's--
[MUGINO]
Hamazura!
I've been looking for
you all over the place!
It's exhausting lugging
around this baggage!
You're not gonna make me do
this to you too, are you?
She betrayed ITEM.
Okay, what's going on here?
Just go!
You're not going to force me to
hide behind a child like this!
Get out of here right now!
Please go.
If we wait too much longer,
she's gonna die.
I've wasted a lot of
time just worrying.
I'm done with that!
I know this is what I wanna do,
but I can't protect her alone.
So you have to take her away.
If you don't, everything
will go up in smoke
right in front of us.
[MUGINO chuckles]
Electrifying,
isn't it, Hamazura?
How did you get that?
[HAMAZURA]
It doesn't matter.
Because you won't be
able to force Takitsubo
to use her ability
without it, will you?
[laughs]
Try to catch me,
you psychotic hag!
[crash]
Hamazura.
Run all you want, it won't
be long before I kill you.
[MUGINO]
Mmm... Nice place.
I can understand why you
would wanna choose
an unmanned facility.
It's definitely
the perfect choice
when you're about to die alone.
Your time is up, Hamazura!
[MUGINO]
This is ridiculous.
Stop making things so difficult.
Just hand over
the Ability Crystals
and we'll call it a day.
[grunts]
I hope you realize
I'm not going to rest
until I kill every single
member of SCHOOL.
So give me the crystals.
[HAMAZURA]
I refuse!
I won't let Takitsubo
use them anymore.
[MUGINO]
What?
She's already reached
her limit with them!
You think it matters if she has?
Once she's all spent,
I'll just recruit another
esper to replace her.
Well, then again,
she is the only one
who can actually search AIM
diffusion fields for us.
I guess it's fine if another
esper does it differently--
as long as I always
know where those
SCHOOL bastards are.
I'm sorry, but I can't
work with you anymore.
You'll never be able
to beat Kakine.
You've already run away
from him twice now.
It appears that you have
a couple of screws loose
in that thick head
of yours, Hamazura.
Let me tighten them!
[HAMAZURA]
She said...
Takitsubo said she
didn't want me to die.
Why? When I've been
such a selfish jerk?
It's up to me to make sure
someone like her
finds happiness!
[MUGINO screams]
I give you a Level Zero ear.
In exchange for a
Level Five eyeball.
Now that's a bargain,
am I right?
Hamazura!
It doesn't make any difference!
Rip off my arms and legs,
or tear up my internal organs,
it wouldn't change how
outclassed you are!
I am a Level Five,
do you hear me?
I could kill a hundred
of you Level Zeros
without having to lift a finger!
[HAMAZURA] Then what does
this say about me?
Well, that was easy.
Ms. Level Five.
Damn. I really did get the
better end of that deal, huh?
Hamazura.
Hamazura!
[yells]
It's Hamazura.
Um. I don't need
Antiskill's help anymore.
Yeah. It's all over.
So, has there been any progress
on the data analysis
of the tweezers?
There has. But it's no use.
Nothing we've uncovered in
all of our research so far
is going to be enough to put me
on equal footing with Aleister.
We'll just have to
make another push.
Then you're gonna
do it, aren't you?
[KAKINE] I'll kill the
top-ranked guy in Academy City.
[phone ringing]
Yeah?
[SHADOWY MAN]
Excellent work.
BLOCK's plot to assassinate
a governing board chairman
has failed.
It pleases me greatly to have
such capable subordinates.
[ACCELERATOR]
Tch.
Sounds like you wanna
get killed pretty badly.
[SHADOWY MAN]
Not at all.
I am genuinely
grateful for this.
Which is why I'd like to offer
some valuable information
as a personal reward.
Specifically regarding
a threat to the life
of Serial Number
20,001, Last Order.
[gasps]
By the way, what ever
happened to the lost child?
Is your crazy hair still getting
all those tickley feelings,
or did they go away?
"Misaka doesn't have crazy
hair," answers Misaka Misaka
as she starts to wither
from exhaustion.
"Hmm.
I'm pretty positive they were
wandering around here earlier,"
says Misaka Misaka.
"But then they went
somewhere else," she added,
still tired from all
that walking she did.
Ah!
"Misaka really wants
one of those, too!"
says Misaka Misaka
with excitement
even though she has no money.
But Misaka has a thought,
and turns toward Uiharu
with a sparkle in her eye.
Aw. How can I resist?
[UIHARU]
Here.
Be sure to come back right
after you're done, okay?
[UIHARU sighs]
Oh, well.
In the meantime, I'll just enjoy
having some of this sundae.
[KAKINE]
Please pardon the interruption.
I'm trying to find this girl.
Have you seen her?
Sorry, I'm afraid I haven't.
You should file a report
with an Antiskill station
as soon as possible, though.
You're right.
That's a great idea.
Thanks.
Oh, and, Miss? There's
something I forgot to mention.
[gasps]
[KAKINE] I know Last Order was
just here, you little airhead!
Guess I should've
said that to start!
[KAKINE] Where is she now?
Tell me, and I'll let you go.
You'll never find her.
[KAKINE]
Huh?
Could you not hear me up there?
I said she's in a place where
you'll never be able to find her
no matter how hard you look.
Ha!
Very well, then.
This is where we'll say goodbye.
Ha.
You showed up much sooner
than I was expecting.
Oh, man. What is this crap?
Don't get all worked up
playing these pathetic
games, Third-string.
[ACCELERATOR]
Huh?
[ACCELERATOR] Not a good
look for you, Fairy-boy.
I know what it looks like.
Don't you worry.
Yes, let's focus on something
that'll be useful to you.
You need to learn to act more
like a villain and I can help!
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
[KAKINE]
Fun fact.
Did you know that
everything in the universe
is made up of
elementary particles?
It's true.
Although, that particular rule
doesn't apply to my Dark Matter.
Because what I've
produced doesn't exist.
At all. Anywhere
in the universe.
And I don't mean that it
should theoretically exist
and we just haven't
discovered it yet,
or some crap like that.
What I'm saying is that
it actually doesn't exist.
And, of course, matter
that doesn't exist
operates under laws
that don't exist.
For example, turning
light from the sun
into rays that are strong
enough to kill a man.
All right. I'm ready.
[gasps]
Hey, Accelerator!
You claim to have the ability
to reflect anything,
but that's not quite
accurate, is it?
You unconsciously filter
out what's harmful
and what's beneficial.
And then choose to reflect only
that which you don't need.
My ability affected the
sun and wind just now.
I injected them with
25,000 vectors each.
And depending on how
those were reflected,
I just have to attack you
by using vector fronts
from among those you've
unconsciously accepted.
[KAKINE]
This is Dark Matter.
A space with foreign
matter in the mix,
and a place you
know nothing about!
[yells]
[KAKINE]
I'm going to gain the right
to deal directly with Aleister!
And that's what the
tweezers were for.
But it looks like killing
you will be a lot quicker,
Mr. Top-Rank.
Oh, please.
At this point, is the
order of our ranking
really that important?
Aleister's a fan of fail-safes
and always moves multiple
plans forward concurrently.
But he also comes prepared
with an alternative option
for each of them.
And I am the alternative
option for you!
[ACCELERATOR] Oh, so you
think getting rid of me
automatically shoots you to
the top of the totem pole?
[KAKINE]
That's right.
If I'm at the center of it all,
Aleister can't
ignore me anymore.
Tch. Are you kidding me?
I have no idea what
happened to you in life
that finally broke you down,
but when you use
it as your cause
and say that that's what
makes it okay for you
to go about killing civilians,
you've cheapened
yourself as a villain.
Oh, I'm sorry, how many
civilians did you smash up
while battling me
at the café earlier?
[chuckles]
I knew you'd make
that comparison
because you have
absolutely no aesthetic.
And by the way, do you
have any idea at all
why you and I are
currently divided
into first and second ranks?
It's because there's a
complete wall between us
that you'll never get past!
[gasps]
What? No way.
So you were defending all those
people while we were fighting?
Yeah, well, screw you!
How much control do
you actually have?
Aw, did that make
you a little angry?
That's what real villains do!
[growls] This is my
world, Accelerator!
No, it is not!
I'm redefining this world
as being made up
of elementary particles,
and that includes
your Dark Matter.
And once I crack your
formula, that's checkmate.
You think you've got me figured
out to the core, don't you?
[ACCELERATOR] Your core's
not that deep, trust me.
There's not very
much to figure out.
[ACCELERATOR]
See ya later, Third-string.
[laughs]
At least it's not as pathetic as
being beaten by the good guys.
[YOMIKAWA]
Stop! Don't shoot!
Just calm down and
hand me the gun.
What in the world could you
possibly need one of those for?
I'm a villain. I need weapons.
Then I'm gonna have to stop you.
Do you really mean that?
You're not giving me
any other choice,
so I need you to hear me.
I am never going
to give up on you.
I will drag you out of
the dark if I have to.
That's why I'm here
standing in your way.
I do it for the children
I have to protect,
and for the peace
I love so much.
I see a place where you are.
You're there with Last Order.
We're all living together,
laughing and having fun.
Isn't the gun you're
holding in your hand
detrimental to the
manifestation of that future?
I know you're not a complete
villain at heart, Accelerator.
[thud]
I guess we're the same.
Neither one of us has the
ability to protect anyone.
Isn't that right?
Plus.
You've sent plenty of people
to their deaths already--
just like your friend here!
[gasps]
[screams]
[KAKINE laughing]
Damn. Impressive evil.
I always knew you had it in you.
I'm speechless.
Seeing this, I get why Dark
Matter was the alternative plan.
I'm trying really hard not to
get too excited about this.
I mean, do we have to
fight to the finish now?
[laughing]
[yelling]
[KAKINE]
What the hell?
[gasping]
So that's what you
were used for?
Is this your true
form or some--?
Lower your weapons, men!
The only way to
stop him is by...
[LAST ORDER]
"I found him."
[LAST ORDER] "That's my lost
child," says Misaka Misaka,
insisting on speaking with you.
[yells]
[growling]
"It's gonna be all right,"
says Misaka Misaka
as she stretches out her hand.
Accelerator. Was that you?
[MALE ANTISKILL 06A gasps]
[MALE ANTISKILL 06A]
Fire!
[screams]
Stop now!
"There, there. You don't have
to do this anymore. 'Kay?"
says Misaka Misaka,
stating what's right.
[growls]
[screams]
[LAST ORDER]
"It's okay. It's done.
And thank goodness,"
says Misaka Misaka.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Apparently,
the SCHOOL organization
needed the tweezers.
They used it to recover a
very important nanodevice.
[ACCELERATOR]
What does that even mean?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Well, it means
that a roughly 50-million-unit
surveillance nanodevice
was dispersed by Aleister
throughout the air
of Academy City.
"The Underline."
That's what it's called.
It's a nexus that makes up
an intelligence network.
Which directly connects
Aleister to anything
regarding Academy City.
So, you can probably guess
the level of information
that each unit holds.
Here it is.
Codes to the city's dark side.
There's GROUP, and SCHOOL,
then ITEM, MEMBER, and BLOCK.
[MUSUJIME]
We know all those organizations.
Yeah, seems a little
after-the-fact.
No, wait, there's
more than just that.
[MUSUJIME, UNABARA]
Hm?
The last one to come
up is called: DRAGON.
[ACCELERATOR] I swear I'm
gonna get the better of them.
On everything.
[KAMIJO] An underground complex
extends beneath Academy City.
A momentary peace is torn
apart when he appears.
Next time, "The Third Level."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.