[FRENCH SORCERERS gasp]
[yelling]
[ACCELERATOR] What's going
on with their power?
It didn't reflect;
it just decomposed.
And not into water,
ice, or steam, either.
Into light.
Is this what that
son of a bitch Aiwass
was talking about
when he mentioned
"a completely
different set of rules
unlike you've ever seen before"?
Tch. What a pain.
I guess I could
beat it out of them.
Hmm...
Electricity?
[ACCELERATOR]
Who are you?
[MISAKA WORST] If I told
you "Third Season,"
would you recognize Misaka?
[ACCELERATOR gasps]
What?
[MISAKA WORST] Misaka doesn't
care about the outcome
of the war.
No orders concerning
that have been input.
Misaka's only objective is
to slaughter the first-ranked.
That's why Misaka has come.
It is the reason,
the only reason,
Misaka was taken out
of her culture solution.
I thought your magical
item had been destroyed.
Nonetheless, I doubt
you've successfully restored
your Divine Retribution.
And even supposing
that you have...
...your resistance is futile.
You won't be able to defeat
me with its methodology.
Hah! A hollow threat
when you as Michael
cannot wield your
full power in this state.
That's true enough.
Compensating for that limitation
is why I need Sasha Kruezhev
and Imagine Breaker.
[VENTO] I know the restrictions
that right arm of yours has
on its use!
You fool.
You've been so busy playing
around with those nobodies.
I bet it's already
disintegrating into the air.
You're the fool.
Are you suggesting that's
enough to make up the gap
between us?
[VENTO] This is where things
start getting interesting.
[GROUP gasps]
[FIAMMA grunts]
[VENTO]
Blind, arrogant idiot.
Are you aware that
Biagio Buzoni commanded
the Queen of the Adriatic
and the Queen's Fleet
escort at Chioggia in Italy?
And did you know that
I am the one who calibrated
one of the Ten Holy Spirit
Spells to a practical level?
True, controlling the entire
Queen of the Adriatic
might not have been possible.
I can't wield that
particular weapon on my own.
However, I do have
the affinity to control
at least a part of the fleet.
Not to mention, I can do this.
I could lecture you about
wasting so many of your shots,
except it's not like
you can hear me.
[FIAMMA]
Is that right?
Actually, I take better
care of my things
than you give me credit for.
[FIAMMA] I may not be able
to avoid it disintegrating
into the air,
but as you can see,
I have managed to secure it
in that state.
I no longer have any
limitations on my power,
and that will be your undoing,
Vento of the Front.
Fiamma!
I don't need destructive force.
I can finish
someone with a touch,
so demolishing my opponent
requires no exertion.
[KAMIJO]
Vento! What's going on?
Silence!
[FIAMMA]
I'm in no hurry.
[VENTO gasps]
I can hit someone with a wave,
so besting my enemy
requires no speed.
[VENTO yells]
Vento!
Stay back!
Come, now, it's not
as though I yanked out
your whole tongue.
I only tore it a little bit.
You're overreacting.
This is bad.
His power is beyond crazy.
So what now?
How're we supposed to beat him?
[VENTO coughs]
What did you--?
[FIAMMA]
It's simple, really.
What I possess isn't
the right arm itself,
but the power that
comes with the right arm.
Can your feeble mind
understand what that means?
I'll help.
It means that I possess
full command over all
the church of the cross's
many supernatural phenomena.
I'll let you imagine the rest.
You're not too inept
to do that much, right?
No, that's impossible.
[FIAMMA]
You're right, of course.
It's still incomplete.
However, because the world
is in such a state of flux,
I can use it even
in this unfinished form.
[VENTO gasps]
Tell me, are you aware of
the full extent of the fallout?
That the four great attributes
have slowly started going awry?
No... You don't mean...
How could I not have known?
The aftershocks of Angel Fall
were truly that serious?
No, actually.
It's thanks to the
distortions in the great laws
that were there to begin with.
Those are what created
the opening for such
a spectacularly powerful
spell to be invoked.
You understand?
Because I would like
to get on with this.
[VENTO gasps]
[KAMIJO yelling]
Oh, no!
[FIAMMA] How many poor
unfortunates have you taken
a stand for at this point?
You know, you really
are a delightful fellow.
The thing I enjoy most
is the way it always
comes back to you.
You're inspired by so many
others to leap headlong
into danger time and again,
but who earns the rewards
from doing so?
Who keeps them all for himself?
You.
What are you trying to say?
I'm simply asking you to
consider whether your actions
are entirely in the
right and utterly devoid
of selfish motivations.
Think about it: I use
the power of my right arm
to sort out whatever
problems I might encounter.
In a similar manner,
you use your right hand
to sort out whatever pesky
incidents might arise
around you.
And we both do it in a way
that shatters with one blow--
something that someone else
has taken desperate pains
to build up.
[laughing]
I have a firm conviction in
myself and in my actions.
I can proceed with
a clean conscience
because I fully believe
that the choices I make
will pave the way
for the absolute good.
So I should give up, then?
Let Index lie there in
agony because you think
you're doing what's right?
Well screw that idea!
All right.
So are you saying you're
good for putting a stop to it?
Whether I'm good or not
isn't the issue here!
I just know that
Index is suffering!
Do you even realize how many
people you're hurting here?
How much damage this war
of yours has caused?
If fighting for a girl who can't
wake up is such a bad thing,
then maybe I don't want
to be on the side of good.
How delightful!
Would you repeat that
to the sweet sister
you've gone to such trouble
to lie to for all this time?
Via this remote
control magical item,
there are periods when our two
consciousnesses become linked.
Which means that sometimes,
the things that I see
and hear are conveyed
to her, as well.
[KAMIJO]
No... Is he saying...?
Now, then, are you going
to tell me you're on the side
of good in that
situation, as well?
You carry on with this
shameless act of yours,
supposedly for her benefit.
Maybe you've convinced yourself
that you're not doing it
for your own self-satisfaction.
But when all is said and done,
will your hypothetically noble
act actually be her salvation?
I can't wait for the
judgment to come down.
I'll be taking this.
[ELIZALINA, LESSAR gasp]
[KAMIJO]
Fiamma!
I would like to bring
you along, too,
but I'm afraid carrying
you both at once would be
rather difficult.
Not to mention, your right
hand would inhibit me
from transporting you.
Speaking of which,
don't get yourself killed.
I'm going to need
that right hand.
[KAMIJO]
Wait!
Damn it.
[FIAMMA]
But when all is said and done,
will your hypothetically noble
act actually be her salvation?
I can't wait for the
judgment to come down.
[HAMAZURA]
How is she?
[DIGURV] It's the effects of
an Academy City-made drug.
This is a small facility.
They don't have the
means to treat it properly.
Makes sense.
Even so, at least she's got
a decent bed to sleep in.
That's more than
I was able to manage.
[CHILD 19A coughing]
[CHILD 19A coughs]
[HAMAZURA chuckles]
I guess since I'm
from Academy City,
the Russian people must
see me as the ultimate enemy.
An enemy wouldn't
offer fuel to help us.
Besides...
The truth is, this place has
always been a questionable area.
Even before World War
Three started.
Problem is, with the
Elizalina Alliance
of Independent Nations'
border not far from here,
the Russian army wants to
raze our homes to the ground
and build a frontline base.
They're greedy for land.
They've even gone so far
as to scatter landmines
throughout the area under
the pretext of preventing
an invasion from the alliance.
You're kidding!
Hey, now, it's not really
as bad as it might seem.
We collect the mines
and give them to an NGO,
and they exchange them
for food or other goods.
[HAMAZURA]
Why am I here?
What exactly am I trying to
find in the middle of this war?
[DIGURV gasps]
Looks like things have
taken a turn for the worse.
Privateers.
[HAMAZURA]
What?
[DIGURV] They're kind of like
officially recognized bandits.
Blank units that exist
within the Russian military
but have no official members.
They take in thugs,
wannabe soldiers,
the type of people
who specialize in doing
the dirty work.
Why send an outfit
like that here?
Hold on, are you saying--?
Yeah. Now's their chance.
They're going to exploit
this war to level our land.
Then we have to get
out of here, now!
Except we don't have
any fuel to drive with.
So then what do we do?
Should we try to run somewhere?
Just hang tight.
I'm working on that.
[ACCELERATOR] This one appears
to be an irregular unit,
created to draw out
and focus the animosity
of the entire Misaka Network.
[ACCELERATOR groans]
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[MISAKA WORST chuckles]
[ACCELERATOR] I already made
the decision not to hurt
any of them ever again.
So I can't use my Reflection.
This is ridiculous.
What did she say?
"Third Season"?
Was this the reason the jerks
of Academy City created her?
For the sole purpose of
mentally tearing me down?
[MISAKA WORST] Don't tell me
you're starting to have
delusions about
protecting Misaka.
Because no one
asked you to do that.
[ACCELERATOR]
Hold on a second.
Something about this
doesn't check out.
All of the Sisters connected
to the Misaka Network
can have their actions shut
down with a single command
from Last Order.
So, sending one of
those units against me
wouldn't make sense.
Which means this one
has to be--a fake!
[ACCELERATOR]
No! She's the real thing!
You should know that
there is a device installed
inside of Misaka's body
which will ensure
that a shutdown command
from Last Order is rejected.
Relying on her would be foolish.
She won't do anything
to stop this Misaka.
So, it's up to you.
If you wanna stop this one,
you'll have to fight
with the intent to kill her.
But you can't do that, can you?
Because if you do, that would
mean all your other efforts
up to now would be
rendered meaningless.
Well, I guess, you'll
just have to sit back
and take your beating.
[laughing]
"I'm so scared.
Help me."
[laughing]
Misaka is going to toss
you around like a toy
until you're unrecognizable!
You'll see! It's going
to be so much fun!
There you go, keep on dodging!
Aren't you the one who killed
over ten thousand Misakas?
Not only once, but over
ten thousand times?
So that means you have
to have your human rights
trampled on at least
ten thousand times
just to balance it out!
And if we factor in interest,
tripling that exchange
won't be enough!
Here! Have another!
[ACCELERATOR yells]
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[MISAKA WORST]
Here's a question for you.
None of the other Misakas,
including Last Order,
have called you out.
Did you ever stop to
wonder why that might be?
If not, you should!
[ACCELERATOR groans]
[MISAKA WORST] It's not that
they decided on their own
not to hate you!
Because believe me, they do.
They just couldn't show it.
They're built with a different
system for processing
human emotions.
Which is to say, it's impossible
for them to understand
or express them!
[laughing]
Little by little,
all your precious Misakas
are becoming more human!
Which means many of them will
realize their hatred very soon!
They'll end up considering
their legitimate right
to vindication!
Let's see.
Maybe Misaka will start with
the damaged goods over there.
That would be much
more effective, anyway.
The Misakas will experience
a drastic overhaul
under Third Season.
The network will be
expanded, redeployed,
and improved overall.
Their performance
will be enhanced,
and breakthroughs will be great.
And then, the older-generation
Last Order will no longer
be needed to call the shots!
[MISAKA WORST yelps]
[ACCELERATOR]
Ah, I see.
So that's the way this
whole thing plays out.
None of us are gonna
get out of this stupid,
screwed-up situation
until somebody dies.
[MISAKA WORST yells]
[MISAKA WORST grunts]
--[bone snaps]
--[yelling]
[ACCELERATOR]
You're done here.
But this isn't how
it ends, is it?
I'm sure one of those other
Sisters will be arriving next.
Or maybe they'll use Yomikawa
or Yoshikawa instead,
and wipe out some completely
irrelevant village or town
without reason.
Well, enough.
I'm not putting up
with it anymore.
Help... Help me.
Someone please help...
Make it stop...
[ACCELERATOR whimpering]
[laughing]
--[beeping]
--[blast]
[ACCELERATOR laughing]
[MISAKA WORST]
It's... your fault.
[grunts] Your... fault.
[ACCELERATOR coughs, retches]
Well, screw a whole
load of that!
Screw it all! Screw it all!
Screw it all!
So...
She was created
and killed for my sake
as a pawn in a twisted
plan to break me.
That's why she was sent!
That's what the scum in
Academy City is after, right?
No matter how much
we've suffered,
this kid has to die, and my
mind has to be blown to pieces!
Meanwhile, some jerks are off
lounging in a nice, warm room!
Probably having a drink
and smiling about
how clever they are.
Congratulating themselves for
putting this whole twisted plan
of theirs into motion.
Well, I'm onto them.
Which means now I'll have
to throw it all back
in their faces!
If the only way their plan will
succeed is if this kid dies,
then I'll make sure
that doesn't happen.
I'll save her life and guarantee
their project's failure!
Watch closely,
you filthy sons of bitches!
I'm done putting up
with your crap.
I'm gonna wipe those smug
expressions off your faces,
starting right now!
Stupid punk-ass, scum-sucking,
dirt-eating sons of bitches!
You rotten bastards think
you have me all figured out,
don't you?
You look down on me and
think all I know how to do
is cause pain and kill!
I'll show you right now that
I am much more than that.
I have what it takes to
protect something, too!
Watch!
Just watch!
[KAMIJO] Black wings cast
a hue over the snowy plain.
Blood-soaked fists
clench tightly.
The mightiest and the
lowliest clash once again.
Next time,
"A Reason to Protect."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.