>> SO YOU'RE HOSHIYOMI, HUH?
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
THAT WAS TOO EASY.
HUH?
>> HA HA HA.
DEMON NINJA, SHADOW INCARNATION.
>> HUH?
>> OH, KAGOME.
>> COULD THE KAGOME THAT WAS
WRITTEN ON THAT SCROLL REALLY
BE ME?
>> HIT THE MARK!
>> AAH!
>> HOJO, TAKE THE KEN BLADE
WITH YOU AND HURRY TO THE
FURAI SHRINE.
>> NO, KAGOME.
I CAN'T LEAVE YOU HERE ALONE
TO FACE THESE DEMON PUPPETS
BY YOURSELF.
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME, NO!
>> HAVEN'T YOU FIGURED IT OUT
YET?
ALL THE POWER YOU THROW AT ME IS
BEING ABSORBED BY THE BLADE.
>> WHAT?
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> OH, THIS AURA IS FROM
HOSHIYOMI'S KON BLADE!
>> YOU'RE OK.
WHERE'S KAGOME?
>> KAGOME WAS--SHE WAS...
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO KAGOME?
>> HA HA HA.
>> KAGOME!
>> WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
DO YOU WANT TO PROTECT THE
KEN BLADE, EVEN IF IT COSTS THIS
WOMAN HER LIFE?
>> KAGOME.
>> KAGOME!
WHY, YOU--
>> HMM.
>> AAH!
>> INUYASHA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> WHAT CAN YOU KILL WITH A
RUSTY SWORD LIKE THAT?
>> MY TESSAIGA.
>> IF YOU REALLY WANT TO GET HER
BACK, COME TO FURAI SHRINE.
OH, AND ONE MORE THING, DON'T
FORGET THE KEN BLADE.
>> KAGOME!
>> HA HA HA HA HA HA.
>> DAMN IT.
COME BACK HERE!
>> INUYASHA!
>> PLEASE LET ME GO WITH YOU.
>> YOU'LL ONLY BE IN THE WAY.
>> TAKE ME ALONG WITH YOU.
>> HOLD ON, YOU TWO.
ACCORDING TO LADY KAEDE,
THE FURAI SHRINE IS THE MOST
EFFECTIVE PLACE TO PURIFY
THE KENKON BLADES.
SO WHY WOULD HE CHOOSE THAT
SHRINE FOR THE EXCHANGE?
>> WOULD YOU GET TO THE POINT?
>> IT HAS TO BE SOME KIND OF
TRAP.
>> WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO STAND
HERE THEORIZING.
KAGOME IS IN DANGER BECAUSE
I GOT HER INVOLVED IN
MY PROBLEMS.
>> YOU THINK?
I'M GOING.
>> WAIT FOR ME!
>> WE'D BETTER GO, TOO.
>> MM-HMM.
KILALA!
>> LET'S GO!
>> WE WILL NOW PROCEED WITH
THE RITUAL TO RESTORE THE
NAGINATA OF KENKON.
DO NOT ALLOW THOSE FOOLS TO GET
NEAR THIS SHRINE.
>> YES, SIRE.
>> SO THEN, LET ME HANDLE THE
HALF-DEMON.
WITH THAT RUSTY SWORD, HE'S NO
THREAT.
>> THEN I WILL TAKE CARE OF THE
MONK.
>> HA HA HA.
I'LL TEAR APART THE WOMAN.
>> HA HA HA HA,
OH, GOODY.
THAT LEAVES THE YOUNG SAMURAI
FOR ME.
>> OVER THERE.
>> WHERE'S THAT LIGHT COMING
FROM?
>> A BARRIER?
>> [YELLING]
>> HA HA HA HA HA HA.
YOU SHALL NOT PASS.
>> YOU SMELL TASTY, YOUNG MISS.
I AM SEIRYU OF THE MOON.
THE PLEASURE IS ALL MINE.
>> SANGO!
WHERE ARE YOU?
>> I'LL TAKE YOU ON, MONK.
>> HEY, SHIPPO, SNAP OUT OF IT.
WAKE UP!
OH, I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE.
GOOD, YOU'RE AWAKE.
WE'VE ALL BECOME SEPARATED.
YOU'VE GOT TO HURRY AND FIND
INUYASHA.
>> RIGHT AWAY.
HUH?
AKITOKI, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I MUST HAVE BRUISED MY BACK
IN THE FALL.
>> SHAPE UP!
>> OH, MY.
SUCH AN ADORABLE BOTTOM.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU ARE ONE HANDSOME SAMURAI.
I'M SUZAKU OF THE FLOWER.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> EW.
>> HEH HEH HEH.
YOU'RE UNFORTUNATE TO HAVE TO
FACE ME--GENBU OF THE DARKNESS.
>> GET OUT OF MY WAY, CREEP.
>> WHAT CAN YOU DO WITH A
USELESS BLADE LIKE THAT?
>> ARE YOU DEAF?
I SAID GET OUT OF MY WAY!
>> HUH?
WAS THAT A MOSQUITO BITE?
NOT WORKING, IS IT?
>> I DON'T EVEN NEED TESSAIGA
TO TAKE YOU DOWN.
CHECK THIS OUT!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> I KEEP TELLING YOU,
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
>> HOW CAN THIS GUY BE SO TOUGH?
>> IS THAT IT?
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
NOW IT'S MY TURN!
[GROWLS]
DEMON NINJA SPINNING DEMON
SHELL!
HA HA!
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE ME!
>> HA HA HA HA.
I HAVEN'T HUNTED A FEMALE IN
AGES.
I'M CERTAINLY GOING TO ENJOY
THIS.
>> UH, YOU'RE DISGUSTING!
HIRAIKOTSU!
WHERE'D HE DISAPPEAR TO?
>> HA HA HA!
DEMON NINJA, PHANTOM SCALES!
AAH!
>> WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT'S HE DOING?
>> DEMON NINJA, STEEL STORM!
>> SANGO, I'M COMING!
>> YOU THINK SO.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET PAST ME FIRST.
>> MY WIND TUNNEL!
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
>> AAH!
>> HA HA HA.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, MONK?
THAT THE BEST YOU CAN DO?
>> COME ON!
>> LET GO!
I WON'T LET YOU HAVE THE
KEN BLADE.
>> STINGY.
IF YOU GIVE ME THE BLADE OF KEN,
I'LL USE THE SKIN OFF YOUR SWEET
FACE TO DECORATE IT.
YOUR DEATH WON'T BE IN VAIN,
I PROMISE.
>> THANKS, BUT NO THANKS.
I LIKE MY FACE WHERE IT IS.
>> CAN'T YOU BE MORE AGREEABLE?
THEN HOW ABOUT I SKIN YOUR FACE
AND MAKE A WALL HANGING OUT
OF IT?
I'LL KISS IT EVERY SINGLE
MORNING.
>> STOP IT.
YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
>> OH, I CAN'T WATCH THIS.
IT'S THE END OF THE WORLD.
>> THAT'S IT.
I GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
FOX FIRE!
>> [YELLING]
AH, HOT, HOT, HOT!
>> THERE!
>> YOU SAVED ME.
>> THAT WASN'T VERY NICE.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO?
AAH!
>> [YELLS]
I DIDN'T MEAN IT AT ALL!
WATCH!
WATCH IT!
>> YOU'VE AWOKEN.
>> THIS MAN'S EYES...
THEY'RE SO SAD.
>> YOUNG LADY, EXPLAIN
SOMETHING.
WHY IS A HUMAN LIKE YOU
TRAVELING WITH THAT HALF-DEMON?
WHAT ARE YOU TO HIM?
>> WHY DO YOU ASK ME THAT?
'CAUSE IT'S NONE OF YOUR
BUSINESS.
>> HUMANS AND DEMONS HAVE NO
LOVE FOR EACH OTHER.
THERE CAN NEVER BE A LASTING
BOND BETWEEN HUMANS AND DEMONS.
THAT IS BECAUSE HUMANS ALWAYS
END UP BETRAYING DEMONS.
YOU, TOO, WILL BETRAY THAT
HALF-DEMON.
>> NO, THAT'LL NEVER HAPPEN.
>> HUMANS ARE WEAK CREATURES.
THEY ARE WEAK IN BODY AND SOUL.
EVEN THOUGH THEY ARE WEAK,
THEY TRY TO LIVE PROUDLY.
THAT'S WHY HUMANS BETRAY--IN
ORDER TO PROTECT THEMSELVES.
>> YOU OBVIOUSLY DON'T
UNDERSTAND HUMANS.
DO YOU HAVE SOMETHING AGAINST
HUMANS?
THAT MUST BE IT.
THAT'S WHY YOU CAN SAY THINGS
LIKE THAT.
>> HMM.
>> HUH?
A FEMALE SAMURAI?
WHO IS THAT IN THE PAINTING?
>> TSUKIYOMI.
TSUKIYOMI, WHY HAVE YOU COME?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> HOSHIYOMI...
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
>> TSUKIYOMI!
>> [SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
>> WHY?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
[YELLING]
TSUKIYOMI!
WHY?
AAH!
I WAS SEALED IN HERE BY
TSUKIYOMI.
AS FOR THE NAGINATA OF KENKON,
THE KEN BLADE WAS TAKEN TO
MOUNT FUJI TO THE HOJO FAMILY,
AND THE KON BLADE WAS TAKEN
TO MOUNT HAKUREI.
THEN MOUNT HAKUREI COLLAPSED.
AND THAT'S WHEN I TOOK BACK THIS
KON BLADE.
>> THAT'S WHY KAEDE SAID THAT
THE NAGINATA OF KENKON COULD BE
PURIFIED AT FURAI SHRINE.
>> TSUKIYOMI BETRAYED ME.
SHE HAD PROMISED TO LIVE
WITH ME.
>> I'M SURE SHE HAD A REASON
FOR WHAT SHE DID.
>> HA HA.
HUMANS ARE WEAK, AND BECAUSE OF
THAT, THEY STRUGGLE AND BETRAY
OTHERS--ANYTHING IN ORDER
TO SURVIVE.
AND SO MY DESIRE IS TO SAVE
HUMANS FROM THAT STRUGGLE.
>> SAVE HUMANS?
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
>> I WILL RESURRECT THE NAGINATA
OF KENKON, WHICH WAS CREATED
FROM THE CORPSES OF 222 DEMONS,
AND KILL EVERY HUMAN.
>> YOU THINK THAT KILLING HUMANS
IS SAVING THEM?
>> HUMANS ARE BEYOND SAVING,
EXCEPT BY DEATH...SO DEATH IS
THE ONLY WAY TO SAVE ALL OF
HUMANKIND.
>> YOU'RE WRONG!
[GASPS]
>> EXACTLY AS I SUSPECTED.
WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU, I FELT
A SPIRITUAL POWER SIMILAR IN
STRENGTH TO THAT OF TSUKIYOMI.
SO, YOU SEE, THAT'S WHY I DID
NOT TAKE THE KEN BLADE BACK THEN
BUT BROUGHT YOU HERE INSTEAD.
I AM GOING TO USE YOUR SPIRITUAL
POWER IN THE RITUAL TO RESTORE
THE NAGINATA OF KENKON.
>> YOU CAN'T!
MY STRENGTH.
>> DO YOU YEARN FOR IT SO MUCH?
REST ASSURED THE OTHER BLADE
SHALL SOON BE IN MY POSSESSION
AND EVERYTHING WILL FALL INTO
PLACE.
>> HMM?
WHAT?
WHY IS IT SHAKING?
HUH?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[MOANING]
[YELLING]
>> HUH?
THAT'S SOMETHING YOU DON'T SEE
EVERY DAY.
>> DEMON NINJA SHELL CRUSHER!
>> AAH!
>> HA HA HA!
YOU WON'T GET AWAY NOW,
HALF-DEMON!
HA HA HA!
>> HEH HEH HEH HEH.
PLEASE DO NOT WORRY.
REST ASSURED I SHALL TAKE CARE
OF YOUR BODY.
>> MIROKU.
>> SANGO!
>> CONCERNED ABOUT THAT WOMAN?
I WOULDN'T WORRY.
YOU'LL BE REUNITED WITH HER
IN THE NETHERWORLD.
>> CURSE YOU.
YOU'RE THROUGH!
>> TIGER FANG ATTACK!
MONK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO, BUT YOU
CAN'T MOVE A MUSCLE NOW.
>> SHIPPO, YOU HAVE TO PULL
YOURSELF TOGETHER!
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'LL BE ALL OVER FOR US UNLESS
I DO SOMETHING.
AKITOKI, HANG ON!
I'M COMING FOR YOU!
>> SHIPPO, YOU GOT TO HELP ME!
>> HERE--GRAB ON, AKITOKI!
HURRY!
>> YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY FROM
ME, MY ADORABLE LITTLE SAMURAI.
>> OH!
HEY, STOP IT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AAH!
>> HA HA HA!
>> HA HA HA.
I'LL CRUSH YOU TO PIECES.
>> MIROKU.
>> HA HA HA.
>> DAMN IT.
YOU'RE DEAD.
BLADES OF BLOOD!
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> HUH, WHAT THE--
>> SANGO, HURRY AND GRAB ON TO
SOMETHING!
>> MIROKU?
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> THAT?
OH, WHAT THE--AAH!
>> AH--AH--WHAT'S HAPPENING?
AAH!
>> OH, NO!
NO, NO, PLEASE!
DON'T!
NO!
>> SANGO!
YOU OK?
>> YEAH, I'M GONNA BE FINE.
>> MIROKU!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> MORE OR LESS, BUT WE'D BETTER
HURRY AND GET GOING.
WE MUST FIND KAGOME.
>> [MOANING]
HUH--UH!
>> [YELLING]
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, AKITOKI?
>> I'M AFRAID I'VE LET YOU DOWN.
THE KEN BLADE FLEW OFF.
IT'S INSIDE THAT BUILDING.
>> HUH?
WHAT'S THIS?
I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING.
KAGOME.
>> HA HA HA.
AT LAST IT HAS BEEN RESTORED,
THE NAGINATA OF KENKON.
>> OH, NO!
>> ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN.
KENKON SIGNIFIES THE YIN AND
YANG OF HEAVEN AND EARTH.
IT REPRESENTS THE 2 MOST
POWERFUL OPPOSING FORCES IN THE
UNIVERSE.
NOW, SUPPOSE I WERE TO USE THE
POWER OF THE NAGINATA OF KENKON
TO SEVER THE INVISIBLE WALL
WHICH SEPARATES THE TWO?
>> I DON'T NEED A LECTURE.
JUST GIVE KAGOME BACK.
>> HUMANS ARE WEAK, AND THEY
BETRAY OTHERS.
THAT IS WHY ALL HUMANS MUST
PERISH FROM THIS WORLD.
AAH!
>> LOOK!
WHAT IS THAT THING?
>> WE'RE BEING SUCKED IN!
>> HELP ME, INUYASHA!
>> AKITOKI!
>> AAH!
>> I CAN'T USE THE WIND TUNNEL
WHILE HE'S GOT KAGOME.
>> OH, NO.
>> INUYASHA, DOES TESSAIGA
HAVE ITS POWER BACK?
>> DAMN IT, IT'S NO GOOD.
>> PLEASE, KAGOME, FORGIVE ME.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I GOT KAGOME INVOLVED IN THIS,
AND I'M THE ONE WHO LET HER FALL
INTO THE HANDS OF THAT DEMON.
>> THIS IS NO TIME TO BE FEELING
SORRY FOR YOURSELF.
>> HUH?
>> WE'VE GOT TO CONCENTRATE ON
KAGOME AND DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO SAVE HER FROM THAT DEMON.
>> YES, BUT HOW DO WE DO THAT?
>> ESPECIALLY WITHOUT TESSAIGA?
>> ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE IF YOU
WANT IT BAD ENOUGH!
>> HA HA HA HA HA HA!
>> [SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
>> ♪ AGAIN, AGAIN, AGAIN
CAN YOU FEEL IT
AGAIN, AGAIN, AGAIN
CAN YOU DREAM IT
>> [SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
>> COME MY WAY
>> COME CLOSE TO ME
>> [SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
SO COME MY WAY
>> COME MY WAY ♪
>> I WILL NEVER FORGIVE HUMANS.
WHY DID TSUKIYOMI SEAL ME AWAY?
>> I WANTED YOU TO REMEMBER.
>> TSUKIYOMI.
>> I WANTED TO REMIND YOU OF THE
KINDNESS YOU SHOWED DURING THE
TIME WE SPENT TOGETHER.
>> THE POWER OF LOVE, ISN'T THAT
CAPABLE OF CONQUERING THE
SADNESS ENVELOPED IN THOSE
TERRIBLE BLADES?
NEXT TIME: ETERNAL LOVE,
THE NAGINATA OF KENKON.
>> THERE MUST BE AN EVERLASTING
DREAM THAT NEVER FADES AWAY,
EVEN IF IT NEVER COMES TRUE.