- HALF-DEMON INUYASHA
IS AFTER THE POWER
OF THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL.
THANKS TO HIS FATHER'S SWORD,
TETSUSAIGA,
HE WAS ABLE TO DEFEAT
HIS OLDER BROTHER SESSHOMARU.
NOW INUYASHA'S EVEN MORE
DETERMINED TO BECOME FULL-DEMON.
AS INUYASHA KEEPS COLLECTING
SHARDS OF THE JEWEL,
KAEDE HAS SAID
I HAVE TO BE CAREFUL.
BUT IT'S OK,
BECAUSE EVEN THOUGH
HE HAS TETSUSAIGA,
I'VE GOT MY OWN WEAPON.
INUYASHA...
SIT, BOY.
[SIGHS]
OH, WOW.
THAT WAS SO NICE.
THE WATER IS CLEAN.
THE AIR IS FRESH.
IT'S NOT SO BAD
BEING IN THE MIDDLE AGES.
- WE'VE BEEN AWAY
FOR 3 DAYS NOW.
YOU SAID
IF WE LEFT THE VILLAGE
WE'D FIND MORE JEWEL PIECES
OUT HERE IN MUSASHI.
BUT--
- YEAH, YEAH.
SURE, WHATEVER.
- ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME,
OR WHAT?
- UH...WELL,
YES, OF COURSE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I WAS JUST A BIT DISTRACTED BY
OUR YOUNG LADY OUT THERE.
- LISTEN, YOU...
- I'M JUST GONNA GO
CHECK ON HER, OK?
- YOU'RE JUST
GONNA GET CLOBBERED.
I WOULDN'T DO IT
IF I WERE--
- LORD INUYASHA!
YOU NAUGHTY BOY.
YOU CAN'T RESIST, EITHER.
- HUH?
AAH!
JEEZ, WOULD YOU NOT
SCARE ME LIKE THAT?
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
IT WASN'T 'CAUSE OF YOU,
IT'S MY CLOTHES!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
- I HEARD A WHISTLE.
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
- THAT'S MY GOOD BOY.
SO WHAT'D YOU BRING ME
THIS TIME?
THIS ISN'T SOMETHING TO EAT!
- OH.
- HEY!
- GIVE ME MY CLOTHES BACK.
- WHO ARE YOU?
YOU LOOK SUSPICIOUS.
- WE WERE JUST ABOUT TO SAY
THE SAME THING.
- YOU MUST HAVE
REALLY BEEN HUNGRY.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME TEA?
- THANK YOU.
- AND THERE'S SOMETHING
IN HERE FOR YOU, TOO.
- NO, THANK YOU.
- BUT IF YOU EAT IT,
I DON'T HAVE TO CARRY IT.
- LOOK, IT'S NOT MY FAULT
YOU GOTTA CARRY AROUND
SO MUCH JUNK ALL THE TIME.
- IT'S NOT JUNK.
IT'S HOMEWORK AND CLOTHES AND--
[SIGHS]
- I GIVE UP.
- I GIVE YOU THANKS, WOMAN.
THE CHIPS POTATO
WERE DELICIOUS.
- MY NAME IS KAGOME
AND HIS IS INUYASHA AND--
[SUCKING]
[MUTTERING]
HE'S MYOGA THE FLEA.
- WHO--WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
- YOU SAID BEFORE
YOU WERE SEPARATED
FROM YOUR ALLIES.
TELL ME,
ARE YOU A NOBLEMAN?
- I'M NOT AT LIBERTY
TO REVEAL MY FAMILY...
BUT MY NAME'S NOBUNAGA.
- NOBUNAGA!
THE NOBUNAGA?
LET ME SHAKE YOUR HAND.
I'M SO GLAD TO MEET YOU.
CAN I HAVE YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
- UH, OK.
- RIGHT HERE,
IF YOU'D BE SO KIND.
AND YOUR FULL NAME,
OF COURSE.
[GIGGLES]
- WHAT'S GOT YOU SO EXCITED?
- THAT'S ODA NOBUNAGA!
HELLO! DIDN'T YOU
STUDY HISTORY?
- WELL, ACTUALLY, MY DEAR,
THAT'S NOT WHAT
THE SIGNATURE SAYS.
- AMARI NOBUNAGA?
BUT I THOUGHT
YOU WERE ODA NOBUNAGA.
- I BELONG TO THE TAKAEDA CLAN
IN THE LAND OF KAI.
PLEASE DO NOT
CONFUSE ME WITH HIM.
- SO YOU DO KNOW HIM?
- YEAH! AND HE'S A BIG IDIOT!
- IF YOU WEREN'T
OBA NOBUNAGA,
THEN YOU SHOULD HAVE SAID SO.
AND HERE I THOUGHT
YOU WERE LIVING HISTORY.
[CLEARS THROAT]
- I TRUST YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
AN IMPORTANT MISSION
DEMANDS MY IMMEDIATE ATTENTION.
FAREWELL.
- I WOULDN'T GO THAT WAY
IF I WERE--
[NOBUNAGA SHOUTS]
I TOLD YOU,
BUT YOU WOULDN'T LISTEN.
- A LOSER? YES.
BUT ODA NOBUNAGA?
PROBABLY NOT.
- HAVEN'T THEY
TAKEN ENOUGH YOUNG WOMEN
AWAY FROM OUR VILLAGE
ALREADY?
- OF ALL THE GIRLS
SUMMONED TO THE CASTLE,
NOT A ONE HAS YET TO RETURN.
- A-HA! I KNEW IT.
SO THE RUMORS I HEARD
WERE TRUE AFTER ALL.
- SO WHY WAS IT
THAT YOU AND ME
HAD TO FOLLOW
AFTER THIS GUY AGAIN?
- BECAUSE HE NEEDS US
AND WE CAN'T LEAVE HIM ALONE.
- WHAT ABOUT US?
WE STILL HAVE
OUR OWN MISSION.
- I WOULDN'T
WANT IT REPEATED,
BUT THEY SAY
THE LORD'S BEEN POSSESSED
BY SOME KIND OF DEMON.
- DEMON?
[THROATY LAUGHTER]
- LIKE YE WELL CASTLE LIFE,
MY PRINCESS?
- YES, MY LORD.
I LACK FOR NOTHING.
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT, THEN.
- IF I MAY, MY LORD.
- YES, PRINCESS.
- THE YOUNG WOMEN, MY LORD,
THE ONES YOUR HIGHNESS
HAS SO GENEROUSLY SUMMONED
HERE TO THE CASTLE,
MIGHT I ASK WHERE THEY ARE?
- YOU MAY NOT!
- FORGIVE ME.
I HAD NO RIGHT TO ASK.
[CACKLES]
[WHIMPERS]
OH, THAT I MIGHT
RETURN TO KAI.
- THAT'S THE PLACE.
- HUH. I SMELL
THE DEMON-STINK FROM HERE.
THERE'S A PIECE
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
THERE, ALL RIGHT.
WE BETTER GO
AND HAVE A CLOSER LOOK.
JUMP ON, KAGOME.
- OK.
- HUH?
HEY, WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
GET OFF!
- I'VE GOT BUSINESS
UP THERE.
- THEN GO FIND
YOUR OWN RIDE.
- JUST DO IT, WILL YA?
- APPRECIATE IT.
- WHY DOES IT ALWAYS
GOTTA BE ME
WHO'S THE NICE GUY?
YOU READY?
[SNORING]
- WELL, SO MUCH
FOR CASTLE SECURITY.
LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE ALL ASLEEP.
- DON'T BE FOOLED,
LORD INUYASHA.
THEIR SLEEP IS HYPNOTIC,
NOT NATURAL.
POSSIBLY,
IT MAY EVEN BE CASTLE-WIDE.
- PRINCESS!
PRINCESS TSUYU!
PRINCESS TSUYU,
WHERE ARE YOU?
IT IS I, NOBUNAGA,
COME TO SAVE YOU!
PRINCESS! PRINCESS TSUYU!
- SHOULD WE BE LETTING HIM
MAKE SO MUCH NOISE LIKE THAT?
- DON'T KNOW WHY NOT.
THEY'RE ASLEEP, AIN'T THEY?
BESIDES, THE SOONER
WE FIND THE DEMON,
THE SOONER WE FIND THE JEWEL.
- PRINCESS!
[GASPS]
PRINCESS TSUYU!
PRINCESS, BE BRAVE.
[GASPS]
- OH, WHAT HAS HAPPENED?
- HEY, NOBUNAGA?
I HATE TO INTERRUPT,
BUT ISN'T THIS
THE PRINCESS OVER HERE?
- HMM?
[GASPS]
- DID SOMEBODY
SAY "PRINCESS"?
I KNOW A GOOD WAY
TO WAKE HER UP.
WHOOP!
YUMMY.
[SUCKING]
- PRINCESS.
- NOBUNAGA?
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
PRINCESS TSUYU,
YOU REMEMBER ME?
OF COURSE I DO.
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
YOU AND I
WERE FRIENDS AS CHILDREN,
AND YOU WERE ALWAYS
SO VERY KIND.
- I--I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
I JUST THOUGHT
YOU WOULDN'T REMEMBER
A LOWLY VASSAL LIKE ME.
- I REMEMBER EVERYTHING:
HOW YOU'D SLIP AND FALL
IN THE POND,
HOW I'D LAUGH AND LAUGH
WHEN YOU FELL IN HORSE DUNG.
- HEY, INUYASHA,
YOU DON'T SUPPOSE
HE'S IN LOVE
WITH THE PRINCESS, DO YOU?
- HUH. PATHETIC.
- IF ONLY I COULD GO HOME.
- PRINCESS.
- IT WAS SHORTLY AFTER
I CAME HERE AS HIS BRIDE
THAT MY LORD HUSBAND
BEGAN TO ACT STRANGELY.
HE'D FALLEN INTO
THE GARDEN POND
AND RAN A TERRIBLE FEVER.
IT WAS AS THOUGH HE HAD BECOME
A DIFFERENT PERSON.
NOBUNAGA,
WHATEVER SHALL I DO?
- THERE SEEMS NO CHOICE.
YOU MUST RETURN TO KAI.
EVEN YOUR FATHER,
SO FAR FROM HERE,
HAS HEARD OF
THE LORD'S DERANGEMENT.
INDEED,
IT WAS HIS WISH I COME
THAT YOU MIGHT BE
RETURNED TO HIM.
- YOU CAME
ON MY FATHER'S ORDERS?
- EVEN IF HE HAD NOT
ORDERED IT,
STILL I WOULD
SOMEHOW HAVE COME.
- NOBUNAGA.
- YES, MY PRINCESS?
I'M LISTENING.
- NOBUNAGA,
THERE'S A MONKEY
ON YOUR HEAD.
- YES, PRINCESS.
- HMM?
SOUNDS LIKE
HE'S FINALLY HERE.
YOU COMING, KAGOME?
- YEP.
- I THOUGHT
I HEARD SOMETHING!
- YECH.
- YEAH, AND IT TOOK YOU
LONG ENOUGH.
LET'S GO.
LET'S SEE YOUR TRUE FACE!
- WHOA!
- EEW! IT'S A TOAD!
- MY LORD?
- I HAVE YOU, PRINCESS.
DON'T WORRY.
[CHUCKLING]
- A PIECE OF THE JEWEL.
I SAW IT!
- YEAH, AND A FAT LOT
OF GOOD IT'S DONE HIM.
- NOT SO FAST, LORD INUYASHA.
HE'S THE 99th TOAD
OF THE 99th GENERATION.
HE'S STRONGER
THAN HE LOOKS.
- THEN ONE GOOD PUNCH
OUGHTA MAKE IT 100.
[COUGHS]
- KAGOME! TOXIC FUMES--
VERY DANGEROUS.
- YEAH, I KIND OF FIGURED THAT.
[COUGHING]
- GIVE ME BACK
MY PRINCESS.
- STAY BACK, MONSTER!
- VERY FUNNY.
AS THOUGH YOU COULD STOP ME,
HUMAN SCUM.
- NOBUNAGA!
PRINCESS!
- PRINCESS!
- NOBUNAGA, STAY STILL--
YOUR SHOULDER.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT HAPPENS TO ME.
PLEASE, YOU'VE GOTTA
SAVE THE PRINCESS.
- I KNEW IT.
SO YOU ARE IN LOVE
WITH THE PRINCESS THEN,
AREN'T YOU, NOBUNAGA?
- HOW COULD YOU TELL?
- YOU MEAN IT WAS A SECRET?
- LOUSY, STINKIN' TOAD.
NO WAY IS HE GETTING AWAY.
[TSUYU SCREAMS]
I'M GOING AHEAD.
COME BACK!
- HEY!
[CHUCKLES]
- PRINCESS, MY PRINCESS.
I COULD EAT YOU UP.
[WHIMPERING]
- HA! I KNEW I'D FIND YOU.
HUH?
- TOO LATE.
- WHAT--WHAT HAS HE DONE?
- PRINCESS TSUYU!
[THROATY LAUGHTER]
- SEALED HER IN LIKE TOAD SPAWN,
JUST AS THE RUMORS SAID.
YOUNG WOMEN KEPT IN EGG SACS
UNTIL THEIR SOULS RIPEN,
THEN EATEN.
WITH THE POWER
OF THE JEWEL SHARD
IN THE YOUNG LORD'S
POSSESSION,
NO ONE COULD OPPOSE HIM.
- YOU MEAN THAT THING
IS GOING TO EAT PRINCESS TSUYU?
NOT WHILE I'M ALIVE!
- POISON GAS! WATCH OUT!
LET'S SEE HOW YOU LIKE THIS.
- LOOK, HE HIT HIM!
- NOT ONLY THAT,
HE WAS ABLE TO USE
TETSUSAIGA TO DO IT, TOO.
- RIGHT,
BECAUSE SHE'S HUMAN.
- I'LL DISSECT YOU WITH THIS
IF I HAVE TO
AND CUT OUT THE JEWEL MYSELF.
- NO. I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
COME TO ME!
SOULS! SOULS!
I NEED SOULS!
- HUH?
[THROATY LAUGHTER]
- I LIVE AGAIN.
- HIS CUT--COMPLETELY GONE.
- FILTHY, NO-GOOD--
- WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
FOR EACH CUT YOU MAKE
I'LL TAKE ANOTHER SOUL.
- HUH?
- PRINCESS TSUYU,
TALK TO ME.
[WHIMPERS]
[COUGHS]
[GASPS]
PRINCESS.
- NOBUNAGA. NOBUNAGA!
PRINCESS TSUYU.
NOW I DIE WITHOUT REGRET.
- DON'T YOU TOUCH
MY PRINCESS.
- HOLD IT!
- YOU GOT NOTHING TO SAY.
- PRINCESS TSUYU,
WHAT HAVE I--
WHERE--WHERE AM--
PLEASE, SOMEONE TELL ME
THIS ISN'T MY DOING.
- WELL, WELL,
ISN'T THAT CONVENIENT.
- THAT VOICE!
IT IS THE VOICE
OF MY KIND LORD HUSBAND.
- SO THEN THAT WOULD MEAN
THE REAL LORD IS STILL ALIVE.
I KNEW IT!
- IT'S LIKE A NIGHTMARE
BUT I CAN'T WAKE UP.
SOMEHOW I KNEW,
DEEP INSIDE,
I REALIZED
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
AND YET I WAS POWERLESS
TO STOP IT.
I WANTED TO,
BUT I COULDN'T.
KILL ME, PLEASE.
- HMM?
- I DON'T THINK
I HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO STOP MYSELF.
- MY LORD.
- DO IT NOW!
PLEASE,
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
- ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU'RE FINALLY
MAKING SENSE.
YOU WANT IT IN THE GUT OR...
DO I TAKE THE HEAD?
- INUYASHA, WAIT.
WHAT ABOUT THE LORD?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR HIM?
THERE'S A HUMAN IN THERE.
- IT'S YOU WHO DIDN'T HEAR.
HE JUST ASKED ME
TO KILL HIM, DIDN'T HE?
THIS AIN'T NO TIME
TO GO ALL MUSHY.
- STOP IT!
- HUH?
- SHEATHE YOUR SWORD,
INUYASHA, PLEASE!
INSIDE THIS MONSTER,
THE REAL LORD'S HEART
IS STILL BEATING.
- WHY YOU--
MOVE IT LITTLE MAN,
OR I'LL KILL YOU, TOO.
- PLEASE, DON'T!
- THEN MOVE IT.
- I CAN'T.
I CANNOT LET YOU KILL HIM
WHILE THE REAL LORD'S
STILL IN THERE.
BESIDES, EVEN IF
IT WASN'T IN THERE,
I CAN'T APPROVE
OF YOUR TAKING LIFE.
- NOBUNAGA...
- I REALIZE IT'S CRAZY
IN TODAY'S WORLD
TO FEEL THIS WAY,
BUT I CAN'T HELP IT.
I CAN'T!
- HMM.
HMM.
HAVE IT YOUR WAY.
I'LL LET YOU
SETTLE IT YOURSELF.
THE RESPONSIBILITY
IS YOURS NOW.
HMPH!
- INUYASHA.
[LAUGHTER]
- THANK YOU FOR SPARING ME.
AAH!
- NOBUNAGA!
YOU CHANGED BACK AGAIN!
- NOBUNAGA?
NOBUNAGA?
- INUYASHA?
- I'LL HELP, ALL RIGHT,
BUT ONLY
IF I GET TO KILL HIM.
- PRINCESS TSUYU.
- LADY KAGOME,
TAKE THE PRINCESS.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- UH, OK. LET'S GO.
COME ON!
- NOBUNAGA!
- GET OFF!
- WELL, HOW 'BOUT IT?
YOU WANT I SHOULD
KILL HIM YET?
- NO. NO KILLING.
- IDIOT.
- PRINCESS.
- HMPH!
- THINK.
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMETHING.
- A MONSTER TOAD
IS STILL JUST A TOAD.
TRY SOMETHING HOT.
- HOT?
- LIKE HOT WATER
OR SOMETHING.
- WATER!
- WELL, SURE.
DISTRACT THE TOAD,
AND THE LORD CAN COME OUT.
- TELL ME,
HOW DO YOU SUGGEST
I GET THIS HOT WATER?
- WAIT!
- AAH! HE'S COMING!
- SOMETHING HOT!
SOMETHING HOT!
FIRE'S HOT!
IS THERE, LIKE,
A TORCH OR SOMETHING
AROUND HERE?
- I...
- NOBUNAGA'S MONKEY?
WHEN DID HE...
- WAIT FOR ME!
I'M GONNA EAT
BOTH OF YOU!
- WHAT A SMART MONKEY
YOU ARE!
IF ONLY IT WEREN'T SO SMALL.
- MMM.
- AAH!
- YOU STILL IN THERE,
TOAD LORD?
- INUYASHA?
- KAGOME, I'M SORRY,
BUT MERCY'S A LUXURY
WE CANNOT AFFORD.
- LUXURY?
THEN...I KNOW!
AS IN HAIRSPRAY!
IT'LL WORK.
I CAN STILL SAVE HIM.
- THIS IS IT--
THE ONLY WAY.
- SIT, BOY!
- AAH!
- HE CAME OUT!
INUYASHA, GET THE JEWEL.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M ON IT.
DIE, STINKIN' TOAD!
- INUYASHA! INUYASHA!
WELL DONE.
THE LORD IS STILL SAFE.
YOU DROVE OUT THE TOAD.
YOU WORRIED ME FOR A BIT,
BUT THEN YOU CAME THROUGH.
- ACTUALLY, I, UH...
- IT'S KINDER
JUST TO LET HIM BELIEVE IT.
- NOBUNAGA?
- PRINCESS TSUYU.
- NOBUNAGA!
- PRINCESS TSUYU!
- YOU SAVE MY HUSBAND.
THANK YOU.
- PRINCESS TSUYU.
- OH, MY LORD,
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT.
IT'S AS THOUGH
YOU WERE NEVER AWAY.
- I'M SO SORRY
I WORRIED YOU.
- HE SEEMS A NICE ENOUGH GUY.
- HE HAD HIS CHANCE.
- WITH THE TOAD GONE,
ALL THE GIRLS WERE SAFE.
ISN'T THAT NICE?
- OH, COME ON.
SAY SOMETHING, NOBUNAGA.
WON'T YOU?
- IDIOT.
EVEN THOUGH HE PRACTICALLY
GOT HIMSELF KILLED,
HE WENT OUT OF HIS WAY
TO SAVE THE LIFE
OF HIS ONLY ROMANTIC RIVAL.
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS]
- THAT'S ME, ALL RIGHT.
AMARI NOBUNAGA,
WORLD'S BIGGEST IDIOT
AND FOOL.
- YOU ARE AN IDIOT,
BUT YOU ALSO SAVED
A LOT OF LIVES.
SO DON'T BEAT YOURSELF UP.
THERE'S PLENTY OF OTHERS
WHO WILL DO THAT.
- KNOW WHAT?
THAT DOES CHEER ME UP.
OK.
- HEY, WAIT! LOOK OUT!
- WOULDN'T GO THAT WAY
IF I WERE...
YOU.
- HE'S AN IDIOT, ALL RIGHT.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- SO YOU COME OUT OF THE WELL
AND IT'S THE WARRING STATES ERA
OF JAPAN.
MAYBE I'LL GET TO MEET
SOME REAL LIFE WARLORDS
LIKE NOBUNAGA OR HIDEYOSHI.
I BET I'LL GET AN "A"
IN HISTORY,
BUT I STILL DON'T GO ANYWHERE
WITHOUT AN AUTOGRAPH BOOK.
DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD GET A CAMERA?
DEMONS ARE PRETTY SCARY
IN GENERAL,
BUT SOMETIMES THERE'S CUTE ONES,
LIKE HIM, FOR EXAMPLE.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!