>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS
BETWEEN US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> DEMON RATS GO ON A WILD
STAMPEDE.
JUST WHAT IS NARAKU PLANNING
BY CAUSING THIS?
AND KOHAKU, THE ONE WHO
MANIPULATES THESE RATS, COMES
TO A DECISION AFTER MUCH
ANGUISH.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> A FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
"INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> I SEE YOU'RE NOT HEALED YET,
HAKUDOUSHI.
>> IT'S BECAUSE OF THAT ARROW.
>> UNH!
GO!
>> NARAKU!
>> THAT VERY SAME ARROW BROKE MY
BARRIER ONCE BEFORE, YOU KNOW.
>> THEN KIKYO MUST BE ALIVE.
ONLY SHE COULD IMBUE AN ARROW
WITH SO MUCH SPIRITUAL POWER
THAT IT COULD DO THIS.
>> YOU SHOULD GO IMMEDIATELY AND
KILL HER.
>> [THINKING] I CANNOT SENSE HER
PRESENCE.
PERHAPS SHE IS TRYING TO HIDE
HERSELF.
THAT WOULD SUGGEST SHE IS NOT
FULLY RECOVERED THEN.
I MUST NOW LURE HER OUT AND
DESTROY HER.
>> [THINKING] THERE'S NO
MISTAKING IT.
THAT INFANT, HAKUDOUSHI'S OTHER
HALF, IS NARAKU AND HAKUDOUSHI'S
HEART.
>> [THINKING] NEITHER NARAKU NOR
HAKUDOUSHI HAVE DIED.
IS IT BECAUSE THEY ARE DEMONS?
WHAT MUST I DO TO DESTROY
NARAKU?
>> HEY, KOHAKU.
>> HUH?
>> I ASSUME THAT YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN TOLD ABOUT IT.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> THE TRUTH ABOUT THAT INFANT.
AFTER YOU TOOK IT FROM THE
CASTLE, WHERE WERE YOU SUPPOSED
TO TAKE IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
[THINKING] THAT INFANT, EVEN IF
IT MEANT KILLING EVERYONE IN THE
CASTLE, I WAS ORDERED TO TAKE IT
AWAY FROM THERE.
>> UNH!
>> IF YOU KNEW WHERE IT WAS,
THEN WHAT?
>> I'VE TOLD YOU MANY TIMES
BEFORE THAT ONE DAY NARAKU WILL
REMOVE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
FROM YOUR BODY, AND YOU'LL DIE.
IF NARAKU ISN'T KILLED, THEN
YOUR LIFE CAN'T BE SAVED.
>> [THINKING] IF THE INFANT IS
FOUND, CAN NARAKU BE KILLED?
IT SEEMS OBVIOUS THAT KAGURA
WANTS TO BETRAY NARAKU, BUT...
I'M SORRY, I DON'T KNOW.
>> HMM.
IS THAT SO?
>> [THINKING] I CAN'T LET THEM
FIND OUT THAT I'VE REMEMBERED
EVERYTHING, AND THAT I WANT TO
KILL NARAKU.
IF I KEEP PRETENDING TO BE A
SLAVE, I'LL EVENTUALLY COME
ACROSS THAT INFANT AGAIN.
UNTIL THAT TIME, I MUST NOT
DISOBEY NARAKU'S ORDERS.
>> STEP RIGHT UP, MY GOOD
PEOPLE!
COME ON, DON'T BE SHY!
AND WATCH!
WITH THIS AMAZING SWORD, I SHALL
CUT THIS SHEET OF PAPER FROM ONE
INTO TWO, THEN TWO INTO 4, 4
INTO 8, 16, 32, AND 64 PIECES!
>> I WONDER WHERE INUYASHA HAD
TO GO SO QUICKLY WITHOUT TAKING
US ALONG?
>> WHAT? SHIPPO.
>> WHO CAN SAY?
>> HE WENT TO FIND KIKYO.
HE WENT TO THE SPOT WHERE HE
LAST SAW HER.
>> THAT'S STUPID.
OOH!
>> HE CAN DO WHATEVER HE WANTS.
>> INUYASHA.
>> KIKYO.
YOU'VE HIDDEN YOURSELF AWAY
AGAIN.
WHICH MEANS YOU HAVEN'T REGAINED
ALL OF YOUR STRENGTH YET.
>> INUYASHA'S BEEN GONE A LONG
TIME.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, KAGOME?
DO YOU THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD
HAVE GONE WITH INUYASHA?
>> HE PROBABLY WANTED TO TALK TO
KIKYO ALONE, SHIPPO.
>> HOW COME YOU'RE NOT UPSET
ABOUT ANY OF THIS, KAGOME?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THAT INUYASHA IS SUCH AN
IDIOT!
YOU'D THINK HE'D KNOW BETTER
THAN TO KEEP RUNNING OFF ALL THE
TIME AFTER A GIRL WHO'S LONG
GONE!
THEY DO SAY THAT A PET DOG
ALWAYS REMEMBERS ITS FIRST
OWNER.
OW!
>> WHO YOU CALLING A PET?
>> SO, WHAT DID YOU TALK ABOUT?
>> WE DIDN'T TALK.
SHE WASN'T THERE.
>> YOU CAN TELL ME THE TRUTH,
YOU KNOW.
>> HUH?
WHY WOULDN'T I TELL YOU THE
TRUTH, KAGOME?
QUIT BEING SO STUPID!
>> SIT, BOY.
>> UNH!
WHY, YOU...
>> SIT, BOY.
>> UNH!
>> LISTEN, I WAS NICE ENOUGH TO
LET YOU GO OFF BY YOURSELF.
SIT, BOY.
>> UNH!
>> SO AT LEAST LET ME KNOW WHAT
YOU TALKED ABOUT!
SIT, BOY!
>> UNH!
>> WHY DO I BOTHER HAVING ANY
CONSIDERATION FOR YOU AT ALL?!
SIT, BOY!
>> UNH!
>> IT WOULD APPEAR SHE WASN'T
JUST TAKING IT ALL IN STRIDE.
>> I CAN'T SAY I BLAME HER.
>> POOR KAGOME MUST REALLY BE
HURTING.
>> SHE'S HURTING?
>> HERE.
I GOT IT FOR YOU JUST LIKE
YOU ASKED.
>> HAKUDOUSHI, GO LURE OUT
KIKYO.
AND TAKE ALONG KOHAKU.
DO AS HAKUDOUSHI TELLS YOU.
>> YES.
>> HOW YOU GO ABOUT IT IS UP
TO YOU, JUST MAKE SURE THAT
KIKYO CANNOT STAY IN HIDING.
>> RIGHT.
[GNAWING]
>> SO YOU LET YOUR FOLLOWERS EAT
THE MEAT OF THEIR PREY, AND THEN
DEVOUR THE BONES YOURSELF.
YOU ARE ZUSHI NEZUMI, RIGHT?
>> HMM.
WELL, WELL, LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
A SURVIVOR.
BUT DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'LL SEE THAT YOU'RE REUNITED
WITH THE OTHERS!
[ROARS]
>> WELL, IT SEEMS YOU'RE QUITE
SKILLED, KOHAKU.
TAKE THAT LITTLE SHRINE FROM THE
CREATURE'S BACK.
>> YES.
UNH!
>> BY THE WAY, IF IT OPENS
ACCIDENTALLY, YOU'LL DIE.
[CHITTERING]
[HAKUDOUSHI LAUGHING]
>> AH!
[CHITTERING]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
[CHILDREN SHOUTING]
>> HUH?
>> WHAT IS THAT?
OH, NO!
AAH!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
>> TELL ME, DO YOU SENSE
SOMETHING STRANGE?
>> HMM?
>> SOMEONE'S COMING!
>> PLEASE, SOMEBODY HELP US!
PLEASE!
>> FASTER, GRANDPA!
>> ARE THEY BEING PURSUED BY
SOMETHING?
>> OH, NO.
>> WHAT IS IT?
[CHITTERING]
>> A HORDE OF DEMON RATS!
>> INUYASHA!
PLEASE, WAIT!
>> WHY?
WHAT THE--
>> THERE'S MORE.
>> I KNEW IT.
ZUSHI NEZUMI.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T KILL THEM.
THE MORE OF THESE THINGS YOU
KILL, THE MORE THEY INCREASE.
>> THEN HOW DO YOU DESTROY THEM?
>> WITH A SPECIAL TOXIC SMOKE,
BUT YOU NEED THE RIGHT
INGREDIENTS.
>> DO YOU HAVE THEM WITH YOU?
>> UNFORTUNATELY NOT.
>> THEN I GUESS THIS IS OUR ONLY
CHOICE.
WIND TUNNEL!
>> YOUR VILLAGE WAS ATTACKED?
>> YES.
LUCKILY, MY GRANDSON AND I WERE
UP IN THE MOUNTAIN BEHIND THE
VILLAGE.
THE OTHERS WERE NOT SO LUCKY.
[SOBBING]
>> GRANDPA!
[CRYING]
>> TELL ME, SANGO, WHERE DO
THESE ZUSHI NEZUMI COME FROM?
>> THERE'S USUALLY A LARGE DEMON
WHO'S THEIR CHIEF.
HE KEEPS THE RATS IN A MINIATURE
SHRINE, WHICH HE CARRIES ON HIS
BACK, AND HE RELEASES THEM TO
KILL HUMANS AND ANIMALS.
BUT HE ONLY ATTACKS WHAT HE
INTENDS TO EAT.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF A LARGE PACK
OF RATS ATTACKING A VILLAGE.
>> HMM?
THERE'S A LOT MORE OF THEM.
THEIR SCENT IS COMING FROM FAR
OFF, AND IT'S AS THOUGH THEIR
NUMBERS ARE STEADILY INCREASING.
>> INCREASING?!
>> YOU TWO MUST GET MUCH FURTHER
AWAY.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> HMM!
WE'RE GOING TO LOOK AROUND A BIT
AND SEE WHAT'S HAPPENING.
[THINKING] I CAN SMELL THEM.
THE WAY THEY'RE INCREASING
ISN'T NORMAL.
WHAT THE HECK IS GOING ON?
[CHITTERING]
[HAKUDOUSHI LAUGHING]
THEY JUST KEEP COMING, DON'T
THEY?
THE RATS WILL SCATTER
EVERYWHERE, AND THEY'LL DEVOUR
ALL THE HUMANS.
>> HUH?
[CHITTERING]
>> RATS!
[SCREAMING]
>> AND AS THEY DO, THEIR NUMBERS
WILL ONLY INCREASE.
BEFORE VERY LONG, THIS LAND WILL
BE DEVOURED BY RATS.
>> SO YOU THINK THIS WILL MAKE
KIKYO COME OUT OF HIDING?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
I SUPPOSE SHE WILL SOONER OR
LATER, AS SOON AS SHE REALIZES
WHAT IS HAPPENING.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'D RESORT
TO THIS, JUST TO LURE KIKYO OUT
OF HIDING.
[CHITTERING]
>> KOCHO.
>> YES?
>> THERE IS SOMETHING I REQUIRE.
IT IS IN THE WESTERN MOUNTAINS.
[CHITTERING]
>> THESE FILTHY RATS HAVE
OVERRUN THE WHOLE REGION.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND YOU SAY WE HAVE NO WAY TO
BATTLE THE SWARMING HORDES
DIRECTLY?
>> NO, THEY DON'T DIE, EVEN IF
YOU SLAY THEM, SO THEY KEEP
INCREASING.
AND SINCE THEY'VE SPREAD SO FAR,
WE CAN'T TRACE THE SOURCE.
>> BY SOURCE YOU MEAN THE
MINIATURE SHRINE?
>> YES.
I HEARD THAT IF YOU DESTROY THE
SHRINE, THE RATS WILL DISAPPEAR.
>> MIROKU AND SANGO HAVE BEEN
GONE A LONG TIME.
>> GEEZ, WHY DO I HAVE TO WAIT
INSIDE THIS BARRIER, TOO?
IT'S COMPLETELY STUPID!
>> WHEN YOU GET MAD, YOU GO
CRAZY AND SWING YOUR SWORD
AROUND.
THAT WILL ONLY MAKE THE RATS
INCREASE.
>> SO, THEN, SHIPPO, ARE YOU
IMPLYING THAT I'M STUPID?
>> WOW, FOR SOMEONE WHO'S
STUPID, YOU FIGURED IT OUT
QUICKLY.
UNH!
[SHIPPO CRYING]
>> INUYASHA! UP THERE!
>> SAIMYOSHO!
>> DOES THAT MEAN THAT NARAKU IS
BEHIND THE RAMPAGE OF THE DEMON
RATS?
>> HAH!
I FIGURED HE'D HAVE TO BE
BEHIND THIS SOMEHOW.
I DIDN'T THINK HE'D DIE IN THAT
FIGHT.
>> OH, LOOK WHAT THE CAT
DRAGGED IN.
>> WELL, NOW WE KNOW ONE THING
FOR CERTAIN, THAT NARAKU IS
SOMEHOW INVOLVED.
>> HMM.
>> I WONDER IF THIS MEANS THAT
NARAKU IS TRYING TO FIND US SO
HE CAN SEND HIS WRATH TO EAT US.
>> I'M NOT SO SURE.
I'VE GOT A SNEAKING SUSPICION
THAT HE WANTS US TO KNOW THAT
HE'S THE ONE BEHIND ALL OF THIS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> IT SEEMS TO ME AS THOUGH HE'S
TRYING TO LURE SOMEONE OUT INTO
THE OPEN, BUT NOT US.
SOMEONE ELSE.
>> HUH? KIKYO.
>> [THINKING] HE'S RIGHT.
NARAKU'S AFTER KIKYO.
>> LADY KIKYO.
KOCHO HAS RETURNED.
>> HERE, LADY KIKYO, I BROUGHT
IT FOR YOU.
THE BRANCH OF OGATAMA THAT YOU
ASKED ME TO FIND.
>> GOOD.
ASKA, KOCHO, IT IS TIME TO
LEAVE.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> LOOKS LIKE THE SCATTERED
HORDES OF RATS ARE BEGINNING TO
GATHER.
>> THEY SEEM TO BE HEADED FOR
ONE PLACE.
>> YES, THEY'RE FORMING ONE
LINE.
>> THIS CAN ONLY MEAN ONE THING.
SOMEONE SOMEWHERE HAS CAST A
MAYOSE.
>> MAYOSE?
>> IT'S A SPELL THAT LURES
DEMONS TOGETHER AND DESTROYS
THEM.
BUT ONLY ONE WITH IMMENSE
SPIRITUAL POWER CAN CAST SUCH A
SPELL.
[THINKING] THE ONLY ONE CAPABLE
OF THIS IS KIKYO.
SO, THEN KIKYO IS AT THE END OF
THIS FLOW OF RATS.
>> OK, INUYASHA, LET'S GET
GOING.
>> HUH? KAGOME?
>> I'M GOING TO TRY TO FIND THE
SOURCE OF WHERE THE RATS ARE
COMING FROM.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> SOMEONE HAS TO.
THE RATS JUST KEEP ON COMING AND
THERE'S NO END IN SIGHT.
WHICH MEANS THAT THE SHRINE IS
STILL RELEASING RATS.
>> SO, WE MUST STOP THE SOURCE
OR IT WILL NOT END.
LET'S SPLIT INTO TWO GROUPS.
I'LL GO ALONG WITH SANGO.
>> HUH?
KIKYO HAS FINALLY MADE HER MOVE.
KOHAKU, I WANT YOU TO STAY HERE.
GUARD THE SHRINE CLOSELY.
AND DON'T CLOSE THE DOORS.
>> YES.
>> HEY, KAGOME, IF KIKYO IS
REALLY UP AHEAD, YOU THINK THAT
NARAKU WILL GO THERE, TOO?
>> HUH?
[THINKING] PROBABLY.
NARAKU WANTS TO TAKE KIKYO
ALIVE.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, SHIPPO?
YOU AFRAID OF NARAKU?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE GONE WITH
MIROKU AND SANGO INSTEAD OF
COMING WITH US.
>> NO WAY.
I GOTTA STAY WITH YOU TWO
BECAUSE WHEN YOU AND KIKYO MEET
AND YOU START ACTING WEIRD,
WHO'S GOING TO BE THERE TO
CONSOLE KAGOME?
DO YOU GET IT, YOU TWO-TIMING
DOG?
>> KEEP IT UP AND I'LL FEED YOU
TO THE RATS.
>> HEY, INUYASHA, LOOK UP AHEAD!
>> HUH?
>> I'M SCARED, GRANDPA.
>> IT'LL BE OK, CHILD.
IT'LL BE OK.
>> [SPEAKING JAPANESE]
>> UHH....
>> COME ON, THINK FAST, SHIPPO.
YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO SCATTER THE
RATS?
>> HOW ABOUT THIS.
FIREFALL OF DEATH!
>> QUICK, GET OUT OF HERE WHILE
YOU CAN.
>> YES, YES, OF COURSE.
>> THANK YOU!
>> HOW WAS THAT?
MY FIREBALLS ARE PRETTY AWESOME,
AREN'T THEY?
>> INUYASHA, LOOK AT THAT.
THE RATS ARE CLIMBING THAT TREE.
>> THAT TREE'S VERY TALL, ISN'T
IT?
YEAH, IT IS.
IT REACHES ALL THE WAY UP INTO
CLOUDS.
>> IT FEELS LIKE THE RATS ARE
DISAPPEARING.
IS THIS THE MAYOSE?
>> LOOKS TO ME AS THOUGH THIS
VILLAGE WAS DEVOURED SOME TIME
AGO.
>> YES, AND JUST BECAUSE IT WAS
IN THE PATH OF THE RATS.
>> IT'S TERRIBLE.
>> KIRARA, LET'S GO.
>> [THINKING] WHY LET MORE
LOOSE?
KIKYO HAS ALREADY COME OUT OF
HIDING.
>> YOU DON'T CLOSE THE DOORS.
>> [THINKING] DAMN HIM.
HE'S DOING THIS FOR HIS OWN
ENJOYMENT.
IF I CLOSE THESE DOORS, THE RATS
WILL STOP.
EVEN NOW, IT MAY SAVE SOME
LIVES.
HUH?
ARGH.
I'M BEING WATCHED.
IF I CLOSE THE DOORS, NARAKU
WILL KNOW THAT MY MEMORY HAS
RETURNED.
>> KOHAKU!
>> HUH?
>> DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE BEHIND
THIS.
>> [THINKING] SISTER.
>> KOHAKU.
ON MY WAY HERE, I SAW SO MANY
VILLAGES DEVOURED BY RATS.
HOW I WISH THAT YOU WERE NOT A
PART OF THIS.
>> UHH...
[THINKING] I CAN'T DISOBEY MY
ORDERS.
>> KOHAKU!
>> SANGO!
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY VILLAGES
WERE DEVOURED JUST TO LURE KIKYO
OUT OF HIDING?
>> WHEN YOU SEE HER, TELL HER
"AS LONG AS YOU KEEP RUNNING
AWAY FROM NARAKU, THIS WILL
HAPPEN OVER AND OVER AGAIN."
>> KOHAKU, YOU'RE GOING TO END
UP DEVOURED BY THE RATS, TOO.
>> I'M SORRY, SISTER,
BUT I CANNOT DISOBEY MY ORDERS.
>> NEXT TIME, KOHAKU'S DECISION
AND SANGO'S HEART.
>> I MUST DEFEAT NARAKU AS SOON
AS POSSIBLE.