- INUYASHA'S SWORD,
THE TETSUSAIGA,
WAS GIVEN TO HIM IN ORDER
TO SUPPRESS HIS DEMONIC NATURE.
UNLESS HE MASTERS HIS WEAPON,
INUYASHA WILL ONCE AGAIN BECOME
A SLAVE TO THE DEMON INSIDE.
UNABLE TO BEAR IT ANY LONGER,
INUYASHA SEEKS TOTOSAI'S COUNSEL
FOR A WAY TO MAKE THE TETSUSAIGA
LIGHTER TO WIELD.
THE ANSWER LAY
IN DEFEATING RYUKOTSUSEI,
THE DEMON WHO HAD BEEN PUT
UNDER SEAL BY INUYASHA'S FATHER.
- UNH!
AAH!
AH!
[GROANING]
- THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO STOP
THE REAWAKENED RYUKOTSUSEI.
HE MUST USE THE BAKURUYUHA,
OR BACKLASH WAVE.
- BACKLASH WAVE?
- A POWERFUL ULTIMATE TECHNIQUE
OF THE TETSUSAIGA.
- IT IS?
BUT INUYASHA CAN'T EVEN
HOLD UP THE TETSUSAIGA,
LET ALONE USE THE WINDSCAR.
HE CAN'T MASTER A NEW TECHNIQUE.
- HUH, I SEE
YOU'RE STILL HANGING ON.
I'LL END YOUR MISERY.
[LAUGHS]
[HEARTBEAT]
[WIND BLOWS]
- INUYASHA'S BECOME SEPARATED
FROM THE TETSUSAIGA!
- INUYASHA, PLEASE WAKE UP!
INUYASHA!
- KAGOME.
[HEARTBEAT]
- HUH?
THE AURA THAT SURROUNDS HIM
IS ENTIRELY TRANSFORMED.
- [GROWLING]
- HA HA! HIS DEMON'S BLOOD
HAS AWAKENED.
SO BE IT.
THIS SHALL PROVE ENTERTAINING.
- [GROWLING]
- OH, NO.
INUYASHA'S ALREADY TRANSFORMED.
- INUYASHA!
- [GROWLING]
- STOP, INUYASHA.
YOU HAVE TO CHANGE BACK.
- [GROWLS]
- WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
IF YOU BATTLE RYUKOTSUSEI
WITH THOSE CLAWS,
YOU MAY COME OUT OF THIS ALIVE.
- YAH!
- YOU MAY BE THE VICTOR.
BUT THE TETSUSAIGA WILL NOT
BECOME LIGHTER FOR YOU.
- [LAUGHING]
- DON'T BE SO SURE OF YOURSELF,
LITTLE MAN.
[LAUGHING]
HUH?
- YAH!
[LAUGHS]
- AMAZING.
- THAT DEMON'S HUGE,
BUT INUYASHA WENT RIGHT FOR HIM.
- IS IT OVER? DID HE BEAT HIM?
- [SIGHS] LET'S RETREAT.
- [GASPS] WHY WOULD WE LEAVE?
- I THINK IT'S OBVIOUS.
INUYASHA HAS CHOSEN
TO FIGHT AS A DEMON.
- SO YOU'LL JUST ABANDON HIM?
COME ON!
- NO, HE'S RIGHT.
I'M AFRAID IF WE STAY HERE,
MASTER INUYASHA
MIGHT EVEN COME AFTER US.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
- WHEN INUYASHA TRANSFORMED,
HE LOST HIS SENSE
OF DISCRIMINATION.
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE
YOU WOULDN'T BE HIS NEXT VICTIM.
- [SIGHS]
I AGREE.
MYOGA, YOU'D BETTER ESCAPE.
- HUH?
- LET ME DOWN, TOTOSAI.
I'M GONNA STAY RIGHT HERE.
- NO, KAGOME. YOU MUSTN'T.
- DON'T. I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA SAY.
ALL OF YOU.
BUT I CAN'T LEAVE HIM.
I CAN'T ABANDON INUYASHA
WHEN HE'S BATTLING FOR HIS LIFE.
PLEASE, TOTOSAI.
YOU HAVE TO LET ME DOWN
RIGHT AWAY!
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU'RE REALLY
THAT DETERMINED.
- WAIT. INUYASHA SURE IS
ACTING STRANGE.
- [GASPS]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- INUYASHA.
- MASTER INUYASHA!
- HE'S TRANSFORMED,
YET HE'S TRYING TO
PICK UP THE TETSUSAIGA.
- COULD IT BE AS KAGOME SAID?
- [HEARTBEAT]
- THERE IS NO DOUBT.
HIS SOUL IS BATTLING
AGAINST THE DEMON BLOOD
THAT RUSHES THROUGH HIS VEINS.
- UNH.
- INUYASHA, YOU CAN DO IT!
- IMPUDENCE! HOW DARE HE THINK
HE CAN CONQUER ME?
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- PLAYTIME IS OVER.
- [GASPS] LOOK OUT!
UNH!
INUYASHA?
- LOOK. WHAT'S THAT?
- HUH?
- THE SHEATH OF TETSUSAIGA.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- A-HA!
THE BARRIER OF THE SHEATH.
- I REMEMBER NOW.
HE USED IT ONCE BEFORE
AGAINST THE THUNDER BROTHERS.
- PRECISELY.
HE USED THE SHEATH TO WITHSTAND
THE LIGHTNING ATTACKS.
- IT SAVED HIM.
THE BARRIER MADE BY THE SHEATH
PROTECTED INUYASHA.
- YES, BUT THERE WILL
NOT BE A SECOND TIME.
THE SHEATH WON'T HOLD.
- YOU CANNOT STOP ME WITH THAT.
NOW, PERISH!
- [GASPS] WATCH OUT!
- WIND TUNNEL!
- MIROKU!
- IT'S TOO STRONG.
- HE DIVERTED IT.
- THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
- [PANTING]
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
IT TOOK EVERY LAST OUNCE
OF MY STRENGTH
JUST TO SLIGHTLY ALTER
THE PATH OF THAT BLAST.
- HOW CAN INUYASHA POSSIBLY HOPE
TO DEFEAT HIM ON HIS OWN?
- UNH.
- HIS DEMON AURA IS DISSIPATING.
- [GROWLING]
- NOBODY DARES
TO STEP ON MY SWORD
AND LIVES TO TELL ABOUT IT!
RYUKOTSUSEI, MY TETSUSAIGA
IS GONNA TAKE YOU DOWN.
UNH!
- [LAUGHS]
YOU'RE SO VERY WEAK.
YOU CAN'T EVEN HOLD UP
THE SWORD.
PITIFUL.
- LAUGH WHILE YOU CAN,
BUT I HAVE MY REASONS
FOR NEEDING TO USE
THE TETSUSAIGA TO SLAY YOU.
- [CHUCKLES]
THIS TIME I WON'T
HOLD BACK FOR YOUR SAKE.
[LAUGHS]
- HUH?
[HEARTBEAT]
- HUH? IT'S NOT MY IMAGINATION.
THE TETSUSAIGA IS
GETTING LIGHTER.
- HMM?
- [GASPS]
- UNH!
- LOOK! INUYASHA CAN
HOLD THE SWORD UP!
- I SEE THAT!
- NOW'S MY CHANCE TO PIERCE
THROUGH RYUKOTSUSEI'S HEART.
AAH!
- YOU FOOL.
HUH?
- GRR!
AAH!
- [SCREAMS]
- [GASPING]
- [RASPY BREATH]
- I DID IT!
- HE PIERCED
RYUKOTSUSEI'S HEART.
- IS HE DEAD?
- UNH!
UH!
- SO LIGHT.
IT USED TO BE SO HEAVY,
BUT NOW IT FEELS LIKE
AN EXTENSION OF MY HAND.
- HOW DARE HE WIELD
HIS SWORD AGAINST ME.
YOU'LL PAY, LITTLE MAN!
- HASN'T THAT UGLY THING
KEELED OVER YET?
- WHAT A DEMON!
STABBED IN THE HEART,
AND HE ACTS
LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED.
- RYUKOTSUSEI WAS A HANDFUL
EVEN FOR INUYASHA'S FATHER,
REMEMBER?
HE WON'T DIE UNLESS
HE'S HACKED INTO PIECES.
- OH, NO!
- NOW IT'S MY TURN!
UNH!
AAH!
- [LAUGHING]
- DAMN! HIS BODY'S HARD AS ROCK.
- I WARNED YOU ONCE BEFORE.
THAT TOY SWORD IS USELESS.
- HUH? WHAT'S GOING ON?
THE SCENT OF THE WINDSCAR.
THE WINDSCAR IS TWISTING
AROUND THE TETSUSAIGA.
HUH?
- YOU'RE THROUGH, LITTLE MAN.
- HUH!
RYUKOTSUSEI, YOU'RE IN
FOR A BIG SURPRISE,
BECAUSE THINGS ARE
GONNA BE DIFFERENT NOW.
HUH!
WINDSCAR!
- [SCREAMING]
- LOOK. THE WINDSCAR.
- AMAZING.
- INUYASHA!
- DID HE BEAT HIM?
- NOT ONLY DID IT GET LIGHTER,
BUT NOW I CAN INVOKE
THE WINDSCAR ANYTIME I WANT.
DID YOU SEE THIS, TOTOSAI?
I WASTED THAT DEMON.
- WELL, I'LL GIVE YOU
THE CREDIT YOU DESERVE,
BUT IT'S TOO EARLY
TO REST ON YOUR LAURELS.
- HUH?
[RUMBLING]
- IS THAT YOUR BEST?
YOU DISAPPOINT ME.
- HUH?
- DID YOU THINK THAT DISMAL
ATTEMPT WOULD DESTROY ME?
- WHAT'S WITH HIM, ANYWAY?
- HE WAS HIT WITH THE WINDSCAR,
AND IT DIDN'T AFFECT HIM AT ALL.
- YUP. DON'T SAY
I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
- I TOLD YOU,
MY BODY IS MUCH HARDER
THAN ARMOR.
NOW IT'S MY TURN.
- UH-OH.
INUYASHA, YOU BETTER
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
HE'S SERIOUS!
- SO AM I.
HUH?
WHAT'S WITH THAT DEMONIC AURA?
- DON'T JUST
STAND THERE TALKING!
HURRY UP AND RUN!
- NO CHANCE.
I'M CONFIDENT I CAN
FINISH HIM OFF THIS TIME.
- JUST BE GLAD YOU CAN
WIELD THE TETSUSAIGA NOW.
LEAVE WHILE YOU'RE AHEAD!
- TOTOSAI'S RIGHT.
- YOU PEOPLE JUST
DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT.
AND BESIDES,
IF I KILL THIS THING,
I'LL SURPASS
MY OLD MAN IN POWER.
UNH!
- SPEAKING OF WHOM,
WHY DON'T YOU GO
AND JOIN HIM IN HELL.
- IT'S HUGE!
- WE'LL ALL GET
CAUGHT UP IN THE BLAST.
KIRARA, MOVE AWAY.
- [YELLS]
- HUH? I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH
A HUGE BLAST OF DEMONIC ENERGY.
- GET OUT OF THERE!
- THE FOOL!
IN ORDER TO DESTROY
RYUKOTSUSEI'S ROCK-HARD BODY,
INUYASHA MUST SUMMON
THE BACKLASH WAVE.
HE DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE.
- I CAN'T AVOID IT!
- [LAUGHING]
YOU CANNOT ESCAPE ME NOW.
- THAT LEAVES ONE CHOICE.
I'VE GOT TO CUT THROUGH IT!
AAH!
- I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH
A HUGE BLAST OF DEMONIC ENERGY.
- [LAUGHING]
YOU CANNOT ESCAPE ME NOW.
- THAT LEAVES ONE CHOICE.
I'VE GOTTA CUT THROUGH IT.
AAH!
- LOOK! WHAT IS THAT?
- HMM? IT CAN'T BE.
- [GASPS]
- INCREDIBLE.
THAT'S THE BACKLASH WAVE.
- I SEE IT.
I NEED TO CUT THROUGH
THAT SMOLDERING SPOT
WITH THE WINDSCAR.
RIGHT ABOUT HERE!
- WHAT?
HIS SWORD HAS TAKEN CONTROL
OF MY ENERGY BLAST.
IMPOSSIBLE!
THIS CANNOT BE!
- AHH!
- THE WHIRLPOOL
AT THE TETSUSAIGA'S AURA
IS PUSHING BACK
RYUKOTSUSEI'S ENERGY BLAST.
- THIS CAN'T BE!
AAH!
AAH! MY BODY!
HE SLASHED MY INVINCIBLE,
ROCK-HARD BODY!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
THAT WAS TOTALLY DIFFERENT
FROM THE OTHER WINDSCARS.
- INUYASHA!
- HUH? KAGOME.
YOU DID IT!
THERE'S HIDE NOR HAIR
LEFT OF THAT RYUKOTSUSEI!
- OH! THAT WAS SO AWESOME!
HOW IN THE WORLD
WERE YOU ABLE TO DO THAT?
- UH, WHO, ME?
- VERY IMPRESSIVE,
MASTER INUYASHA.
I KNEW FROM THE START YOU HAD
THE STRENGTH TO DEFEAT HIM.
- WE HAD TO PRACTICALLY
DRAG HIM BACK HERE.
- HMM.
- I UNDERSTAND NOW, TOTOSAI.
- HMM?
- YOU KNOW, YOU'RE MORE GENEROUS
THAN I GAVE YOU CREDIT FOR.
[LAUGHS]
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO THE TETSUSAIGA, ANYWAY?
IT'S MUCH BETTER THAN BEFORE.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU USED THE TECHNIQUE
WITHOUT REALIZING?
- HUH?
- THE TETSUSAIGA'S
ULTIMATE TECHNIQUE:
THE BACKLASH WAVE.
- THE BACKLASH WAVE? HUH?
- HUH?
YOU'RE SAYING THAT
WAS THE BACKLASH WAVE?
- PRECISELY. LET ME EXPLAIN.
IT USES THE ENEMY'S
BLAST OF DEMONIC ENERGY,
ENSNARING IT WITH THE WINDSCAR
AND REVERSING THE FLOW.
- SO IT ENSNARES
THE ENEMY'S ENERGY
AND SENDS IT BACK AT THEM?
- THE WINDSCAR
AND THE DEMON'S ENERGY BLAST
BECOME LIKE WHIRLPOOLS.
IN OTHER WORDS, THE ENEMY
IS SIMULTANEOUSLY BLASTED
BY THE WINDSCAR
AND BY HIS OWN DEMONIC AURA.
ANYWAY, THAT'S THE THEORY.
- HUH?
- THE TRICK IS HOW TO DISCERN
PRECISELY WHERE TO CUT THROUGH
THE BLAST OF ENERGY,
AND HIS AURA MUST BE
MUCH STRONGER THAN HIS ENEMY'S
FOR THE TECHNIQUE TO SUCCEED.
- I'M SO IMPRESSED, INUYASHA.
- WHY? ALL I DID BACK THERE
WAS USE MY INSTINCTS
AND FOLLOW MY NOSE.
- HMM.
HE'S SURPASSED MERE THEORY.
PERHAPS HE'S DESTINED
FOR GREATER THINGS
THAN I IMAGINED.
- INUYASHA, NOW IT APPEARS
IT WON'T BE SO HARD FOR YOU
TO WIELD THE TETSUSAIGA
IN BATTLE.
- IT'S EVEN BETTER THAN THAT.
HA HA! WATCH THIS!
HERE GOES NOTHING!
AAH!
- THE WINDSCAR.
- WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
I CAN INVOKE THE WINDSCAR
ANYTIME I WANT.
UNH!
AH!
[LAUGHTER]
- AAH! NO!
- HEY, WE GET
YOUR POINT ALREADY.
- THAT'S NOT THE KIND OF THING
YOU WANT TO BE FLINGING AROUND
LIKE SOME KIND OF TOY.
- HA HA!
THERE'S NO ONE
WHO CAN BEAT ME NOW.
I DARE ANYONE TO STOP ME.
- INUYASHA.
- HUH?
- SIT, BOY.
- UNH!
- ONE VICTORY,
AND HE THINKS HE'S INVINCIBLE.
- I'LL SAY. SUCH A SIMPLETON.
- NOT TO MENTION A SHOW-OFF.
- [GROANS]
KAGOME HAD TO SAY IT.
- WELL, HE'S STILL
A RUFFIAN, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- A GIRL NAMED SATSUKI
HOLDS A LONE VIGIL
FOR HER WAR-BOUND BROTHER.
SHE POSSESSES A FRAGMENT
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
AND USES IT AS A CHARM.
IF IT TURNS OUT TO BE REAL,
WE HAVE TO TAKE IT FROM HER.
POOR SHIPPO.
HAS HE FALLEN FOR SATSUKI?
BEFORE WE HAVE TIME
TO FIGURE IT OUT,
A DEMON LAYS A CRUEL TRAP
IN ORDER TO GET
THE FRAGMENT FROM HER.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.