[GRUNTS]
- 50 YEARS AGO, IN ORDER
TO STEAL THE SACRED JEWEL,
NARAKU TRICKED INUYASHA
AND KIKYO INTO BETRAYING
ONE ANOTHER.
- DIE, INUYASHA!
- NOW HE GATHERS
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
AND AS HE DOES SO,
HIS EVIL POWER GROWS.
MIROKU SUFFERS
UNDER NARAKU'S CURSED
WIND TUNNEL IN HIS RIGHT HAND.
- WIND TUNNEL!
- ONE DAY, THE TUNNEL THREATENS
TO DEVOUR MIROKU'S VERY BEING.
HE MUST DESTROY NARAKU
BEFORE THAT HAPPENS.
SANGO'S FATHER AND FELLOW
DEMON SLAYERS WERE KILLED
BEFORE HER VERY EYES.
NARAKU HAD PLAYED A FOUL TRICK,
POSSESSING SANGO'S
BROTHER KOHAKU...
- KOHAKU.
- AND SETTING HIM AGAINST HER.
NARAKU, THE DESPICABLE COWARD
WHO NEVER SULLIES HIS OWN HANDS.
SOMEDAY WE WILL GET HIM.
- SO YOU'RE SUGGESTING
THAT THIS KAGURA WOMAN
MIGHT HAVE BEEN BORN
FROM NARAKU?
- I'M SAYING THAT WE HAVE TO
CONSIDER IT A POSSIBILITY.
- COME ON.
- THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
NARAKU'S A MAN.
HOW COULD A MAN
GIVE BIRTH TO A WOMAN?
- NARAKU HIMSELF WAS CREATED
FROM A HOST OF VARIOUS DEMONS.
WHAT IF ONE OF THEM
WAS TORN FROM HIS BODY?
- GOOD POINT, AND SHE COULDN'T
HAVE BEEN NARAKU IN DISGUISE,
SEEING AS SHE KNEW
SO LITTLE ABOUT US.
- IN ANY CASE,
WHATEVER HER STORY MIGHT BE,
IF SHE'S BEEN CREATED
FROM NARAKU, THEN I'M
NOT INTERESTED IN HER.
- WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE
GONNA GO OUT WITH HER.
- COULD YOU TRY AND STAY
FOCUSED, PLEASE, MIROKU?
- SUCH A FOOL.
I ONLY NEED TO CREATE MORE.
[GRUNTING]
- DIE!
- THE WIND SCAR.
- THE WOMAN HAD
THE SAME SCENT AS NARAKU...
AND THE BURN SCAR ON HER BACK
WAS JUST THE SAME AS HIS.
STILL, DON'T YOU THINK IT'S
STRANGE FOR A WOMAN,
THIS KAGURA, POSSESSED
UNUSUAL STRENGTH?
IF NARAKU COULD CREATE
SOMEONE LIKE HER...
- RIGHT. WHY WOULDN'T HE
HAVE DONE SO MUCH EARLIER?
- THAT'S THE POINT.
IT'S NOT THAT HE DIDN'T
CHOOSE TO DO IT...
- HE WASN'T ABLE TO BEFORE.
- MEANING NARAKU HAS RECENTLY
GAINED SOME KIND OF NEW POWERS?
[DISTANT THUNDER]
- WITH THE BLOWS THAT YOU
RECEIVED FROM TETSUSAIGA,
I WAS ABLE TO COMPREHEND
THE POWER OF INUYASHA'S SWORD.
GO FORTH NOW, KAGURA.
YOUR SISTER KANNA HAS
ALREADY BEEN DISPATCHED.
[INSECTS BUZZING]
- WHERE DID THAT WENCH GET TO?!
HOW DARE SHE RESIST
THE KEEPER OF THE OIL'S
YOUNG MASTER?
ONCE YOU FIND KOHARU,
I EXPECT YOU TO BEAT HER.
- WE'LL CONSIDER IT AN HONOR.
[WHIMPERING]
- WHAT COURSE DO I HAVE?
- OVER THERE!
- IT'S HER!
- WE HAVE FOUND KOHARU!
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
- WHAT MANNER OF BEING
ARE YOU, WENCH?
- THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I WOULD ASK.
YOU SEEM TO BE NO MORE
THAN ORDINARY MEN.
- SHE IS NOT KOHARU, MILORD.
- SUCH BEAUTY.
BRING HER WITH US.
- YES, SIRE.
- YOU WILL COME WITH US.
- RESIST AND YOU SHALL--
- SHE IS IN DANGER.
I MUST HELP.
- NO, YOU DON'T!
AND ONE FOR THE MASTER.
[GROANING]
[HORSE WHINNYING]
- ARE YOU HURT?
- MASTER!
- FORGIVE US, SIRE.
- WE SHALL SEE YOU TREATED.
- THE YOUNG LORD'S FACE
IS BADLY INJURED.
- WHAT WAS THEIR PROBLEM?
- THANK YOU!
- WAS IT YOU THEY WERE AFTER?
- I'M AFRAID SO.
- SANGO!
- SOMETHING WRONG?
- HMM?
[GASPS]
MIROKU!
- HMM?
- IT IS YOU, MASTER MIROKU!
YOU'VE RETURNED!
MIROKU! HOW I'VE MISSED YOU!
- HMM?
- UH...I TAKE IT
WE MET IN THE PAST?
- I AM KOHARU.
- KOHARU...
OH. YOU DON'T SAY?
- FOR 3 LONG YEARS,
I HAVE WAITED.
- KOHARU. I ALMOST DIDN'T
RECOGNIZE YOU.
HOW VERY PROVIDENTIAL,
MEETING YOU LIKE THIS.
- THAT YOUNG GIRL IS
A FRIEND OF MIROKU'S?
- MORE THAN JUST A FRIEND,
JUDGING BY HOW NERVOUS HE LOOKS.
- OH, YEAH!
- I LOST MY PARENTS
AND SIBLINGS IN THE WAR.
THE KEEPER OF THE OIL
TOOK ME UNDER HIS CARE,
BUT WORKED ME DAY AND NIGHT.
I WAS WEARY FROM MY DUTIES,
AND I WEPT EACH NIGHT.
THEN, A WONDROUS DAY.
- HERE. EAT UP.
- A KIND GESTURE FROM YOU,
WHEN YOU HAPPENED BY OUR VILLAGE
TO PERFORM AN EXORCISM.
- SO YOUR NAME IS KOHARU.
AND HOW OLD ARE YOU?
- I'M 11.
- ARE YOU?
KOHARU, WOULD YOU CONSIDER
HAVING MY CHILDREN?
- AAAH!
- UM, IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- YOU'RE DISGUSTING!
HOW COULD YOU LEAD
AN INNOCENT GIRL ON LIKE THAT?!
- YOU LETCH!
- THE HAPPIEST DAY OF MY LIFE.
- OH!
- YOU'D BETTER TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THIS!
- RIGHT.
WOULD IT CHANGE MATTERS
IF I TOLD YOU I HAVEN'T LAID
A FINGER ON THE GIRL?
- THAT SEEMS HARD TO BELIEVE.
- WELL, SHE WAS STILL A CHILD.
- MIROKU HAD TO TAKE LEAVE OF
OUR VILLAGE SHORTLY AFTERWARD.
I KNEW THAT ONE DAY
HE WOULD RETURN FOR ME.
I BELIEVED IT WITH ALL MY HEART.
AS OF LATE,
I NOTICED THE KEEPER
OF THE OIL'S YOUNG LORD
LEERING AT ME.
MY FEARS WERE REALIZED
LAST NIGHT WHEN HE TRIED
TO FORCE HIMSELF ON ME.
- AND THAT'S WHY YOU RAN AWAY?
- YES. I STRUCK HIM
WITH SOME FIREWOOD
UNTIL HE LAY MOTIONLESS.
- OK.
- PLEASE, MIROKU,
WON'T YOU TAKE ME WITH YOU?
- KOHARU.
- I HAVE NOWHERE ELSE TO GO.
BESIDES, I AM AN ADULT NOW.
I AM ABLE TO BEAR YOUR CHILDREN.
[ALL GASP]
- UH, HEH HEH.
- SHE'S EVEN YOUNGER THAN ME.
THINGS REALLY WERE
DIFFERENT BACK THEN.
[SIGHS]
- I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND
OUR POSITION, MIROKU.
WE CAN'T TAKE THAT GIRL WITH US.
- I KNOW.
- STILL, WE CANNOT SIMPLY
ABANDON THE ORPHANED CHILD.
- TRUE ENOUGH.
PERHAPS SHE CAN ACCOMPANY US
UNTIL WE CAN FIND
A SUITABLE FAMILY
THAT CAN TAKE THE GIRL IN.
- AT THE LEAST,
SEEING IT WAS YOU
WHO ASKED HER
TO BEAR YOUR CHILDREN.
- OH, THAT.
I ASK THE SAME QUESTION
EVERY SINGLE TIME I MEET
A NEW GIRL.
- EVERY GIRL EXCEPT ONE, MAYBE.
- SANGO, WOULD YOU CONSIDER
BEARING MY--
- SPARE ME, WOULD YA?!
- SO MIROKU WAS THE FIRST MAN
YOU FELL IN LOVE WITH?
- HE IS. I REMEMBERED HIM
EVERY DAY THAT PASSED.
I KNEW WE'D MEET AGAIN,
AND THE THOUGHT
OF THAT HELPED ME
THROUGH THE HARD TIMES.
- THAT'S FIRST LOVE.
- I AM SO HAPPY.
SO HAPPY I COULD DIE.
[BUZZING]
[COW LOWS]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
- SUCH A PITY.
POOR YOUNG CHILD.
- SO, WOULD YOU BE WILLING
TO TAKE THIS YOUNG GIRL
INTO YOUR VILLAGE, ELDER?
- I WOULD BE HONORED.
LEAVE THE GIRL WITH ME,
YOUNG MONK.
- PLEASE. I PROMISE
NOT TO BE A BURDEN.
LET ME COME.
- NO CHANCE.
- IT WOULD BE DANGEROUS FOR YOU
TO COME ALONG WITH US.
- STOP ARGUING AND STAY BEHIND.
- IT IS IN YOUR BEST INTEREST.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
- HMM.
- PLEASE, KOHARU.
- I HAVE SPOKEN
TO THE VILLAGE ELDER.
- MIROKU.
- KOHARU, COME WITH ME,
WOULD YOU?
- MIROKU, I CANNOT BEAR
TO BE PARTED AGAIN
AFTER SUCH A SHORT TIME.
- TRY TO UNDERSTAND, KOHARU.
I CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT I WOULD
ALWAYS BE ABLE TO PROTECT YOU
IN TIMES OF BATTLE.
YOU SEE, THE DEMON I PURSUE IS
MORE DEVIOUS AND FORMIDABLE
THAN ANY OTHER.
PARTING LIKE THIS IS
DIFFICULT FOR ME, AS WELL.
[SOBBING]
- DOES IT LOOK LIKE HE'S
SETTING HER STRAIGHT?
- FROM UP HERE, IT LOOKS MORE
LIKE HE'S SEDUCING HER.
- LECHER.
HE'S ALL OVER THE GIRL.
A PARTING LIKE THAT WILL
MAKE HER FALL DEEPER IN LOVE.
WHY ARE YOU STARING?
- I MIGHT JUST BE
IMAGINING IT, SANGO,
BUT IS THERE A LITTLE
JEALOUSY THING GOING ON HERE?
- IT'S YOUR IMAGINATION!
- WHOA!
- IF YOU SAY SO.
- MIROKU, I'M BEGGING YOU.
WON'T YOU STAY WITH ME
ONE LAST NIGHT?
- YOU HEARD KOHARU.
WON'T YOU PLEASE STAY
THE NIGHT WITH US?
- NO. I FEAR THAT
POSTPONING OUR DEPARTURE
WILL ONLY MAKE IT
THAT MUCH HARDER FOR HER.
[SOBBING]
- STAY FOR HER SAKE.
ONE LAST NIGHT WON'T MAKE
THAT MUCH DIFFERENCE.
- IT WOULD PROBABLY HELP,
SEEING AS WE'RE THE ONLY
PEOPLE HERE SHE KNOWS.
- I MUST DECLINE.
IF REASON GAVE WAY TO PASSION
AND KOHARU BECAME PREGNANT,
SHE WOULD BE BURDENED
FOR THE REST OF HER LIFE
WITH MY LIKENESS.
[ALL GASP]
- REASON GAVE WAY TO PASSION?
SO WHAT DOES THAT MEAN, MIROKU?
- DELIGHTED YOU ASKED.
- I'M DELIGHTED
YOU WON'T ANSWER!
SHIPPO'S STILL YOUNG,
REMEMBER?!
[KOHARU CRYING]
[SIGHS]
- SHE'S CRYING.
TSK. SHE SHOULDN'T WASTE
HER TEARS ON THAT CREEP.
- INUYASHA?
- FINE! WE'LL STAY HERE TONIGHT
AND SET OUT IN THE MORNING.
BUT NO TEARS IN
THE MORNING, ALL RIGHT?
[GASPS]
- YES!
- WOW.
- MIROKU, HOW IS
THE BATH TEMPERATURE?
- PERFECT. NICE AND HOT.
- AFTER YOU FINISH YOUR BATH,
I SHALL DO MY BEST
TO PREPARE THE FINEST DINNER
FOR YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS.
- THANKS FOR GOING
TO ALL THIS TROUBLE.
- HUH?
- THIS STEW IS INCREDIBLE!
- YOU SAID IT.
KOHARU REALLY IS A SWEETIE.
IT LOOKS LIKE SHE REALLY WENT
OUT OF HER WAY TO PLEASE YOU
WITH HER COOKING, MIROKU.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- WE'RE SURROUNDED.
- PARDON?
- I FEAR THE MEAL KOHARU TOOK
SO MUCH TROUBLE TO PREPARE
WILL GO COLD.
- YEAH.
STRANGE,THOUGH, THAT THERE'S
NO SCENT OF DEMONS IN THE AIR.
- LET'S GO SURVEY THE AREA.
- HUH?
- GET THEM! HURRY!
- IDENTIFY YOURSELVES.
[GROWLING]
- KILL THEM!
- GET THEM! HURRY!
- ARE YOU FROM THE VILLAGE?
- THEY SEEM TO BE UNDER
SOME KIND OF SPELL.
[ALL SHOUTING]
- UNH!
I DON'T THINK SO!
AAH!
- UNH! INUYASHA!
THEY ARE ONLY MORTALS,
NOT DEMONS!
- YEAH, I FIGURED THAT MUCH OUT!
- WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE?
- THEIR NUMBERS ARE GREAT.
I SHALL ASSIST THEM.
- SOMETHING DREADFUL
HAS HAPPENED!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, KOHARU?
- A DEMON GOT INSIDE
AND ATTACKED THE ELDER
AND HIS WIFE.
[GRUNTS, CLEARS THROAT]
- ARE THEY REALLY DEAD?
- THE POOR ELDER.
- A DEMON DID THIS?
- THINK. DO YOU REMEMBER
WHAT THE DEMON LOOKED LIKE?
- NOT EXACTLY.
I ONLY CAUGHT A GLIMPSE OF IT.
- BUT ONE THING
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHY DIDN'T INUYASHA
AND MIROKU SENSE A DEMON?
- HUH?
THERE IT IS!
[GRUNTS]
HUH? SHE VANISHED!
- HUH?
[GASPS]
HIRAIKOTSU!
AAAH!
- SANGO! SHIPPO!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
SANGO! SAY SOMETHING!
HMM?
- KAGOME.
- THAT YOUNG GIRL IS THE DEMON?
KOHARU! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[GRUNTING]
- LOOK INTO MY MIRROR.
GIVE YOUR SOUL.
- HUH...
- INUYASHA! USE RESTRAINT!
THE VILLAGERS ARE UNDER
SOMEONE'S SPELL.
WE MUST NOT HARM THEM.
- WE AREN'T GETTING ANYWHERE!
- YOU FOOLS ARE SO PATHETIC.
- HMM?
- YOU WOULD HAVE DONE WELL
TO SLAY THEM ALL.
THAT WAY, THEY WOULDN'T
KEEP COMING AFTER YOU.
- KAGURA.
- NOT YOU AGAIN.
- THEN AGAIN, I SUPPOSE
IF YOU WERE CAPABLE
OF SLAYING THEM,
YOU WOULD HAVE ALREADY DONE SO.
- ARE YOU THE ONE WHO HAS
POSSESSED THESE VILLAGERS?
- I AM.
A MORTAL WITH NO SOUL IS
NO DIFFERENT FROM A DEAD MAN.
- MORTAL WITH NO SOUL?
- YOUR FRIEND KAGOME IS HAVING
THE SOUL SUCKED OUT OF HER
EVEN AS WE SPEAK.
- YOU WITCH!
- THAT MUST MEAN THAT THERE'S
A SECOND DEMON HERE WITH KAGURA.
- INUYASHA, UNSHEATH
YOUR TETSUSAIGA.
THIS TIME,
VICTORY SHALL BE MINE!
- KAGOME.
- WHAT AILS YOU, INUYASHA?
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE AFRAID.
[SNORTS]
- MIROKU, GO BACK TO THE HOUSE
AND HELP THE GIRLS.
- OF COURSE I WILL.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- YOU KNOW WHAT.
I'M STAYING HERE
TO FINISH THIS WITCH OFF.
- HMM.
[SHOUTS]
- GO NOW, MIROKU!
- I'M ON MY WAY!
- YOUR HELP
WILL ARRIVE TOO LATE!
- THANK YOU, KILLALA.
HUH?
KOHARU! KOHARU!
SAY SOMETHING! KOHARU!
- HMM?
[GASPS]
MIROKU, IT WAS HORRID!
- I'M HERE FOR YOU.
YOU'RE IN SAFE HANDS NOW.
[GROANING]
- HUH?
STOP! WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TO MY FRIEND?
OH!
[GROANING]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- NARAKU CREATES KAGURA
AND KANNA FROM HIS OWN BODY.
A SHARD OF THE SACRED JEWEL
GLIMMERS IN NARAKU'S HAND.
THAT'S THE VERY SAME SHARD
KIKYO STOLE FROM ME.
HOW DID NARAKU GET
HIS HANDS ON IT?
INUYASHA LOSES THE TETSUSAIGA
IN THE FIERCE WINDS CREATED
BY KAGURA.
BETWEEN MIROKU'S WIND TUNNEL
AND MY SACRED ARROW,
WE WILL STOP NARAKU
THIS TIME FOR CERTAIN.
NEXT TIME,
"THE WIND SCAR FAILS."
SEE YOU SOON!