- HMM?
SHOW YOURSELF. I KNOW THAT
YOU'VE BEEN FOLLOWING ME.
- HA HA HA HA!
KIKYO, INUYASHA FEELS BITTER
TOWARD YOU.
HE LIES CLOSE TO DEATH,
AND IT IS ALL BECAUSE
OF MY NEWLY FOUND POWER
FROM THE SACRED JEWEL FRAGMENTS
YOU GAVE ME.
[LAUGHING]
SOON, VERY SOON THE SACRED JEWEL
WILL BE WHOLE ONCE AGAIN.
KIKYO PERSONALLY HANDED
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD TO ME
OF HER OWN FREE WILL.
- WHY, KIKYO?
BY GIVING NARAKU
THE SACRED JEWEL,
HIS EVIL POWERS
HAVE GROWN STRONGER.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
KIKYO, DO YOU HATE ME
THAT MUCH?
KIKYO...KIKYO...
HUH...
[GRUNTS]
- INUYASHA, ARE YOU IN PAIN?
I GUESS THAT'S TO BE EXPECTED.
TETSUSAIGA PROTECTED YOU,
BUT YOU STILL TOOK
THE FULL BRUNT OF THE WIND SCAR.
SANGO'S HURT, TOO.
SHE SHOULDN'T BE MOVED
FOR A WHILE.
SHE MAY TRY TO BRUSH
HER WOUNDS OFF,
BUT SHE DID GET HIT
WITH HER OWN WEAPON.
- AND KAGOME?
- SHE WENT WITH MIROKU TO SEARCH
FOR MEDICINAL HERBS AND FOOD.
- [GROANS]
- [SQUEALS]
- DON'T WORRY, KIRARA.
I'LL GO AND GET HER
SOME COLD WATER NOW.
BOTH INUYASHA AND SANGO
HAVE BROKEN ARMS,
AND TWO TERRIFYING INCARNATIONS
OF NARAKU ARE ROAMING ABOUT.
[SIGHS]
I WONDER HOW WE'RE GONNA GET
OURSELVES OUT OF THIS ONE.
- HMM?
SOUL COLLECTORS.
KIKYO MUST BE SOMEWHERE NEARBY.
- HEY, LET GO OF ME,
YOU SLITHERY DEMONS!
LOOK OUT, INUYASHA!
- KIKYO.
- SHE'LL KILL YOU!
DON'T GO, INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
- KIKYO, I HAVE TO SEE YOU.
UH!
- INUYASHA.
INUYASHA.
- KIKYO.
- YOU'RE STILL ALIVE, I SEE.
I'M GLAD.
- KIKYO, TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON.
IS IT TRUE THAT YOU GAVE
NARAKU ALL THOSE SHARDS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
THAT YOU STOLE FROM KAGOME?
- YES, I DID, TO CAST NARAKU
INTO OBLIVION.
- HUH? WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
NARAKU'S ALREADY A LOT STRONGER
THAN HE USED TO BE,
AND HE'S CREATED
TWO INCARNATIONS FROM HIMSELF--
KAGURA OF THE WIND
AND KANNA OF THE VOID.
- HMM,
SO INUYASHA AND THAT KIKYO WOMAN
KNOW EACH OTHER.
- KAGURA, FOLLOW KIKYO
AND FIND OUT WHAT SHE'S UP TO.
SHE CANNOT BE TRUSTED.
- YOU WANTED ME DEAD.
ISN'T THAT THE REASON
YOU GAVE NARAKU THE SHARDS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL?
- I WOULD NEVER ALLOW
SOMEONE SUCH AS NARAKU
TO TAKE YOUR LIFE.
TAKE HEED, INUYASHA.
NARAKU IS OUR MOST BITTER ENEMY.
- HOW DULL
MERELY SPYING ON THESE TWO.
INUYASHA IS CLOSE TO DEATH.
HE HASN'T EVEN PICKED UP
ON MY SCENT.
I SHALL KILL BOTH KIKYO
AND INUYASHA.
- HMM...
- HUH?
KAGURA!
- YOUR HEAD WILL BE NEXT.
HMM...
SHE ESCAPED.
INUYASHA, NARAKU WILL GROW
ONLY STRONGER AND STRONGER.
- HUH?
- YOU MUSTN'T ALLOW HIM
TO KILL YOU
UNTIL I'M ABLE TO CAST
BOTH NARAKU
AND THE SHIKON JEWEL
FROM THIS WORLD.
YOUR LIFE BELONGS TO ME.
NO ONE ELSE WILL HAVE YOU.
- HUH? KIKYO.
- [PANTING]
SHIPPO, ARE YOU
ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN?
- WAS IT KIKYO'S SOUL COLLECTORS
THAT YOU SAW?
- I'M POSITIVE.
AND THEY LURED INUYASHA
AWAY FROM THE HUT.
- INUYASHA, DID YOU GO
TO MEET KIKYO?
- KAGOME.
- INUYASHA!
[GASPS]
YOU ALL RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
- YOU JERK! SORRY.
YOU SAW KIKYO, DIDN'T YOU?
IT'S WRITTEN ALL OVER YOUR FACE.
HMM.
INUYASHA, YOU CAN'T
EVEN LOOK ME IN THE EYE,
JUST LIKE ALWAYS.
- LISTEN, IT WASN'T LIKE
SOME KIND OF TRYST OR ANYTHING.
- SO HE DID SEE HER.
COME ON. I FIGURED
THAT MUCH OUT MYSELF, STUPID.
- HERE WE GO AGAIN.
MIND YOU, I CAN'T UNDERSTAND
WHY HE DOESN'T WANT TO
GO INTO THE DETAILS.
SO, DID YOU FIND OUT
THE TRUTH?
- HUH?
- DID YOU DISCOVER
WHETHER NARAKU LIED
WHEN HE SAID KIKYO
ACTUALLY GAVE HIM THE SHARDS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL?
- YEAH.
- SO IT'S TRUE, THEN.
SHE MADE A PACT WITH NARAKU.
- NEVER!
UH! I CAN'T SAY
WHAT KIKYO INTENDS TO DO,
BUT I THINK--HUH?
KAGOME'S LEAVING.
NOW WHAT'S HER PROBLEM?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- MY HEART ACHES FOR KAGOME.
- MINE, TOO, ESPECIALLY
CONSIDERING HOW WORRIED
SHE'S BEEN ABOUT INUYASHA.
- HMM? HMM...
- INUYASHA WAS ALMOST
FATALLY INJURED
ALL BECAUSE KIKYO GAVE NARAKU
THE SACRED JEWEL,
AND HE STILL DEFENDS HER.
INUYASHA, YOU'RE SUCH A FOOL.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- SOMETHING IS IN
THE HORSE CORRAL.
- LET'S GO!
- IT'S A DEMON
DEVOURING THE HORSES!
- AAH!
- THAT DEMON IS PATHETIC,
NOTHING MORE THAN
A BRAINLESS GLUTTON.
- HA HA HA HA!
SISTER, YOU WERE JUST THINKING
THAT I AM NO MORE THAN
A BRAINLESS GLUTTON,
WEREN'T YOU?
- HE'S TOYING WITH ME.
THIS DEMON IS ABLE
TO READ MY MIND.
- SANGO, ARE YOU SURE
YOU CAN MOVE?
- I'LL TRY.
- DON'T PUSH YOURSELF TOO HARD.
- WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME MORE MEDICINE
TO RELIEVE THE PAIN?
- I'LL BE FINE.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS
TO STAY HERE.
- KAGURA IS CLOSE,
SO WE HAD BETTER MOVE ON.
- WHY DON'T YOU FORGET ABOUT ME
FOR A WHILE
AND TEND TO INUYASHA'S WOUNDS,
KAGOME?
- I'LL PASS.
HE CAN'T BE TOO HURT,
SEEING AS HE CAN WALK.
- [SIGHS]
DO US ALL A FAVOR
AND APOLOGIZE TO HER.
I DON'T LIKE BEING CAUGHT
IN BETWEEN.
I'D MUCH RATHER BE STROKING
SANGO'S DELICATE, PALE SKIN.
- KEEP YOUR DISTANCE.
- HUH?
- WHAT IS IT, INUYASHA?
- THE SCENT OF A DEAD MAN.
- A DEAD MAN?
- [GROANING]
- HUH?
- A DEMON HAS COME.
IT DEVOURED THE ENTIRE VILLAGE.
- DEMON?
- ON ITS BACK
WAS THE MARK OF THE SPIDER.
- SPIDER?
- ANOTHER REINCARNATION
OF NARAKU.
- PLEASE HELP ME. UH!
- [GASPS]
HAS THAT MAN BEEN DEAD
RIGHT FROM THE BEGINNING?
- KAGURA MUST HAVE BEEN
CONTROLLING HIS BODY WITH
HER DANCE OF THE DEAD.
IT HAS TO BE A TRAP.
- YEAH, A TRAP SET TO FORCE ME
TO MEET THE THIRD DEMON.
- ARE YOU GOING?
DON'T FALL FOR HER TRICKS.
YOUR WOUNDS ARE STILL
FAR TOO SERIOUS.
- I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
- SHE SENT THE DEAD MAN TO US,
WHICH MEANS THAT KAGURA KNOWS
WHERE WE'RE HIDING.
- YES, AND THERE WILL BE
NO CHANCE OF FLEEING.
- I'LL GO AFTER HIM.
HUH! THE DEMON WAS BOUND TO
ATTACK US HERE SOONER OR LATER.
- [SQUAWKS]
- IT'S JUST A FEW CHILDREN.
LET THEM GO.
- NARAKU COMMANDED ME
TO DEVOUR THE ENTIRE VILLAGE,
SO I WILL KILL
EVERY LAST HUMAN
AND EVERY SINGLE COW,
CHICKEN, AND HORSE.
- HMM. DO AS YOU WISH.
I CAN'T BEAR YOUR COMPANY
ANY LONGER.
- [SHUDDERING, CRYING]
- DON'T CRY, YUKI.
THE DEMON WILL NEVER FIND US
IF WE STAY HIDDEN UNDER THE HAY.
- AAH!
HE FOUND US!
- YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD
ESCAPE ME BY HIDING
AMONG SOME STRAW,
NOW, DIDN'T YOU?
- [BOTH SCREAM]
- AND YOU CRIED FOR YOUR MAMA
AND PAPA TO SAVE YOU.
THEY CAN'T HELP YOU NOW,
BECAUSE I DEVOURED THEM BOTH.
I SPEAK THE TRUTH.
LOOK INSIDE MY BELLY AND SEE!
- [BOTH SCREAMING]
- [SHOUTS]
GET OUT OF HERE.
- LOOK AT THAT.
- THE DEMON.
- WITH A SPIDER MARK
ON ITS BACK.
- YOU MUST BE NARAKU'S
THIRD INCARNATION.
- HA HA HA HA!
YOU'RE THINKING
I DODGED THE TETSUSAIGA.
YOU'RE SURPRISED AT MY SPEED
DESPITE MY ENORMOUS SIZE.
- HUH? HE KNOWS
WHAT I'M THINKING.
- HA HA HA HA!
JUST AS YOU SUSPECT,
I AM ABLE TO READ
THE MINDS OF OTHERS, INUYASHA.
MY SISTERS KAGURA AND KANNA
WERE MERELY THE OPENING ACTS.
NOW GOSHINKI MAKES HIS DEBUT.
- HUH! YOUR BIG SPEECH
IS OVER, DEMON.
TIME TO TAKE YOU
OFF THE STAGE!
HUH?
- I TOLD YOU,
I KNOW EVERY THOUGHT
THAT CROSSES YOUR MIND.
YOU SEEM TO BE
SUFFERING GREATLY.
TELL ME, COULD THIS BE
THE END OF YOU?
- NOT VERY LIKELY.
I'M GETTING TIRED OF YOU.
- AAH!
WHAT?
AHH!
- I CAN PREDICT EVERY MOVE
BEFORE YOU MAKE IT.
- [GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA!
- I'LL GO.
HE'S STILL TOO WEAK
TO FIGHT.
[SHOUTS]
- STOP!
IT'S NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS!
- HA HA HA HA!
YOU WERE THINKING
YOU WOULD SUCK ME INTO
YOUR WIND TUNNEL, MONK.
YOU CAN'T, BECAUSE, YOU SEE,
I KNOW ALL OF YOUR WEAKNESSES.
KAGOME, DON'T EVEN CONSIDER
SHOOTING ME WITH YOUR ARROW.
I'LL KILL YOU
BEFORE YOU DRAW THE BOW.
SANGO, YOU ARE UNABLE
TO BATTLE.
YOU STILL CAN'T MOVE
SINCE YOU WERE STRUCK
WITH YOUR OWN WEAPON.
- ME NEXT?
AW...UH! HEY, YOU!
HOW DARE YOU TRY TO IGNORE ME
LIKE THAT!
- DON'T WORRY, SHIPPO.
HE'S JUST TOYING WITH YOU.
- HUH?
THE CHILDREN FROM THE STABLE.
I TOLD YOU TO ESCAPE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING STILL--
OH. THOSE CLOTHES.
DO THEY BELONG
TO YOUR PARENTS?
- UH-HUH.
- JUST BE COOL.
I'LL KILL THIS DEMON
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
THAT'S WHAT YOU WERE THINKING,
CORRECT, INUYASHA?
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
YOU ARE HALF-DEMON,
ARE YOU NOT?
YOU HAVE DEMON BLOOD COURSING
THROUGH YOUR VEINS,
YET YOU TAKE PITY ON HUMANS.
- GET OFF MY BACK!
I'LL SLICE YOU IN HALF!
THE TECHNIQUE THAT BRINGS OUT
THE TETSUSAIGA'S ULTIMATE POWER.
THE WIND SCAR.
- INUYASHA, YOU'RE TRYING TO
SLICE THROUGH THE WIND SCAR
AND BLAST ME AWAY,
ARE YOU NOT?
- IF YOU CAN FIGURE THAT OUT,
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
- THE DEMON HAS DESTROYED
THE WIND SCAR.
- OK, THEN I'LL JUST
SLICE YOUR HEAD IN HALF!
[GASPS]
- YOUR PRECIOUS TETSUSAIGA
IS NOTHING MORE THAN
A DOG FANG NOW.
- [GASPS]
- [BOTH GASP]
- THE TETSUSAIGA IS BROKEN!
- I SUPPOSE THAT PROVES
A DEMON'S FANGS ARE STRONGER
THAN YOUR TETSUSAIGA.
- HUH!
HE BIT IT IN HALF.
HE DESTROYED MY TETSUSAIGA. HUH?
- [SHOUTING]
- AAH!
- INUYASHA, NO!
- HA HA HA HA!
INUYASHA, IT APPEARS THAT
YOUR MIND HAS NOW GONE BLANK.
YOUR SWORD IS BROKEN,
AND SO IS YOUR SPIRIT.
OR ARE YOU DEAD PERHAPS?
- INUYASHA!
- KAGOME!
NO, STAY BACK, KAGOME!
AAH!
UH!
- MIROKU!
- AND YOU, MONK,
YOU WERE PREPARED TO DRAW ME
INTO YOUR WIND TUNNEL,
EVEN IF IT MEANT SACRIFICING
YOUR OWN PATHETIC LIFE.
- MIROKU!
- PLEASE, SAY SOMETHING.
- DON'T RUSH TO YOUR DEATH.
BE ASSURED THAT I PLAN
TO DEVOUR EACH AND EVERY
LAST ONE OF YOU HUMANS.
HA HA HA HA!
AND YOU, KAGOME,
SHALL BE MY FIRST.
- INUYASHA! INUYASHA!
- FOOLISH GIRL.
INUYASHA IS ALREADY--
HUH! WHAT'S THIS?
INUYASHA'S HEART.
AAH!
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG,
GOSHINKI?
I THOUGHT THAT YOU WERE ABLE
TO READ MY MIND.
- UH! INUYASHA!
- WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO INUYASHA'S FACE?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY HAVE YOU TRANSFORMED?
- HOW WOULD I KNOW THAT?
YOU SHOULD BE LESS CONCERNED
ABOUT ME
AND MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT JUDGMENT DAY.
- WHAT'S THE MEANING OF THIS?
HIS HEART IS
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT NOW.
HE HAS NONE OF THE INDECISION
OR SADNESS OR FEAR OF BEFORE.
I SENSE ONLY ANGER,
AND HE DELIGHTS IN THE THOUGHT
OF KILLING ME.
I'LL RIP YOU APART
WITH MY FANGS, YOU HALF-BREED!
- THE DEMON BLOOD
THAT FLOWS THROUGH MY VEINS...
- SILENCE!
- IS UNLIKE YOURS.
- YOU HALF-DEMON!
- I'M IN A CLASS OF MY OWN!
- AAH!
- GOSHINKI, I ENJOYED THAT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO INUYASHA?
- I CAN FEEL THE BLOOD RUSHING
THROUGH MY BODY.
WHY DO I FEEL THIS WAY?
I FEEL THE NEED TO KILL MORE.
- INUYASHA?
- [GROWLS]
STAY AWAY FROM ME!
I CAN'T SAY
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO NEXT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
- THE DEMON IN HIM,
IT'S GOTTEN STRONGER.
- YES, HE'S ALMOST LIKE
A FULL-BLOODED DEMON NOW.
- INUYASHA...
PLEASE.
YOU'VE DESTROYED THE DEMON.
- I SAID STAY AWAY!
- KAGOME!
- DON'T GO NEAR HIM!
KAGOME!
- [GROWLING]
- INUYASHA.
- KAGOME!
- CAREFUL!
- INUYASHA, SIT.
- UH!
- WILL YOU STOP DOING THAT?
- OOH!
- HE'S NORMAL!
- INCREDIBLE.
- HUH?
- THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE BACK!
- UH...
- WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- SESSHOMARU GETS HOLD
OF GOSHINKI'S FANGS
AND HAS A TERRIBLE SWORD FORGED.
KAIJINBO, A SWORDSMITH BANISHED
BY HIS MASTER TOTO-SAI,
CREATES TOKIJIN,
A SWORD EXUDING EVIL.
BUT WHY DOES KAIJINBO
COME AFTER INUYASHA?
NOW THAT HE'S REVERTED
TO HIS HUMAN FORM,
INUYASHA IS IN REAL DANGER.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!