>> HERE WE COME!
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA!"
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> NARAKU, WHO'S BEEN NEWLY
REBORN INSIDE MOUNT HAKUREI,
PRODUCES ANOTHER INCARNATION OF
HIMSELF, AND THEN ESCAPES AFTER
SLAYING KIKYO.
THE TRAGEDY BRINGS DARKNESS INTO
OUR HEARTS.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRYTALE.
>> INUYASHA!
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> UNH!
UNH!
KIKYO!
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT NARAKU
PUT UP THAT HUGE BARRIER AND
HOLED HIMSELF UP IN THAT
MOUNTAIN IN ORDER TO KILL THIS
ONE WOMAN.
>> LADY KIKYO WAS NO ORDINARY
WOMAN.
YOU SEE, NARAKU FEARED KIKYO'S
SPIRITUAL POWERS.
>> NARAKU WANTED TO RID HIMSELF
OF HIS HEART...THE HUMAN HEART
BEATING INSIDE HIM THAT STILL
YEARNED FOR KIKYO.
>> IT'S GREATLY BOTHERED HIM.
NARAKU TRIED TO CUT OUT HIS
HUMAN HEART ONCE BEFORE, I SEEM
TO RECALL.
>> THAT WAS WHEN HE CREATED
MUSOU, THE BEING WHO POSSESSED
THE HEART AND MEMORIES OF THE
BANDIT ONIGUMO.
>> FEAST ON ME, DEMONS.
DEVOUR ME!
AND IN EXCHANGE, BESTOW ME WITH
YOUR MOBILITY AND STRENGTH.
>> THEN NARAKU ABSORBED THE
CREATURE CALLED MUSOU BACK INTO
HIS BODY.
HE FELT IT HAD BEEN TOO SOON TO
RELEASE IT.
>> UNH!
UHH!
KIKYO!
>> [LAUGHTER]
SUCH BITTERNESS.
SUCH FESTERING GREED.
>> THEN THAT MEANS NARAKU WAS...
>> YES.
THOSE INNUMERABLE CLUMPS OF
FLESH WE SAW DEEP INSIDE
MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> HE'S TRYING TO CREATE A BODY
IN WHICH HE CAN SEAL HIS HUMAN
HEART, AND THEN CAST THAT BODY
AWAY.
I SEE.
>> UNH!
>> SO NOW THAT HE'S FINALLY
SUCCEEDED IN KILLING OFF THAT
SCARY PRIESTESS, DOES THAT MEAN
THAT THAT BASTARD NARAKU CAN DO
ANYTHING HE WANTS, WHENEVER
HE WANTS?
WELL, I, FOR ONE, AM NOT GOING
TO LET THAT HAPPEN.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
>> OH!
>> HMM?
>> WE FOUND YOU!
>> WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO CATCH UP
TO YOU FOREVER.
>> GOOD-BYE, KAGOME.
YOU TAKE CARE NOW.
>> YOU TAKE CARE AS WELL, KOGA.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I DON'T HEAR THE MUTT
COMPLAINING LIKE USUAL.
HEY, WHERE IS THAT IDIOT ANYWAY?
HE LOOKED AWFULLY DOWN ABOUT
SOMETHING.
>> THAT STUPID INUYASHA!
HE LEFT KAGOME IN SEARCH OF
KIKYO.
>> PERHAPS INUYASHA HASN'T BEEN
ABLE TO ACCEPT THE REALITY OF
KIKYO'S DEATH.
>> I KNOW HOW HE MUST FEEL,
THEN.
>> [PANTING]
>> INUYASHA...
>> KIKYO!
WHY DID YOU TRY TO FIGHT HIM
ALONE?
WHY DIDN'T YOU WAIT UNTIL
I GOT THERE?
UNH!
UHH!
KIKYO!
EVEN IN THE RIVER, THE MIASMA
ISN'T WEAKENING.
KIKYO...
YOU'RE THERE, AREN'T YOU, KIKYO?
>> I DON'T CARE TO KNOW WHAT
YOUR CONNECTION TO THAT WOMAN
WAS.
THE PERSON RESPONSIBLE FOR
KILLING KIKYO WAS NARAKU.
AND YOU.
YOU ARE THE ONE WHO DIDN'T
SAVE HER.
INUYASHA, BLAME YOURSELF.
>> I WILL SLAY NARAKU MYSELF.
SO YOU WON'T HAVE TO FIGHT
ANYMORE.
I WILL PROTECT YOU.
HUH?
KIKYO.
>> DON'T MOVE.
I'VE LEARNED SOMETHING FROM
WATCHING YOU JUST NOW.
AS LONG AS THE HEART OF THE WEAK
AND PATHETIC ONIGUMO BEATS
WITHIN NARAKU, THERE WILL BE AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR ME.
AND THAT WILL GIVE ME THE CHANCE
I NEED TO TOTALLY DESTROY
NARAKU.
>> KIKYO!
KIKYO DIDN'T BELIEVE IN ME.
THAT'S WHY SHE DIED.
[GROWLING]
UNH!
DAMN IT!
DAMN IT, DAMN IT, DAMN IT,
KIKYO, DID YOU REALLY DIE HERE?
ALL ALONE?
KIKYO...
>> COME ON, KEEP UP THE PACE,
YOU TWO, OR WE'LL NEVER CATCH
NARAKU!
>> THEY SAID A HUGE [INDISTINCT]
WENT SOUTH.
>> FIRST WE GO NORTH, NOW WE GO
BACK SOUTH.
WE SHOULD HAVE JUST STAYED SOUTH
IN THE FIRST PLACE AND WAITED.
>> YES, BUT WITH INUYASHA GONE,
THIS IS THE PERFECT CHANCE FOR
KOGA TO WIN OVER KAGOME'S HEART.
HAVING SAID THAT, HE DID JUST
LEAVE HER BEHIND.
>> I'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND HIM.
>> IF INUYASHA CAN'T DO IT, THEN
I'LL FIND NARAKU AND DESTROY
HIM.
YOU JUST WAIT, KAGOME.
[BIRDS SINGING]
>> IT'S MORNING ALREADY.
INUYASHA, HOW FAR DID YOU GO
IN SEARCH OF KIKYO?
HUH?
INUYASHA.
INUYASHA, HAVE YOU RETURNED?
>> KAGOME?
DID YOU WAIT UP ALL NIGHT
FOR ME?
>> I...
YOU COULDN'T FIND KIKYO,
COULD YOU?
I WANT TO ASK, BUT...
>> I JUST THOUGHT THAT I'D BE
ABLE TO...FIND HER REMAINS,
AT LEAST.
>> INUYASHA...
WHAT CAN I SAY TO HIM?
I CAN'T STAND TO SEE HIM IN
SUCH PAIN.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO CONSOLE HIM.
>> I'M SORRY, KAGOME.
I'M OK NOW.
>> YOU'RE OK?
INUYASHA, YOU DON'T LOOK OK
TO ME AT ALL.
BUT WHAT CAN I DO?
WHAT DO I DO?
[BIRDS SINGING]
>> THIS AREA IS AFFECTED, TOO.
>> YOU MEAN BY MOUNT HAKUREI'S
COLLAPSE?
>> I WONDER IF SHINTARO AND THE
OTHERS ARE OK.
>> [MEWS]
>> KIRARA!
>> HERE YOU GO.
ENJOY.
>> [MEWING]
>> HMM?
>> [MEWS]
>> SHINTARO!
>> HA!
MIROKU, KAGOME!
YOU CAME BACK!
>> YOU'RE ALL LOOKING WELL, IF
I MAY SAY SO.
>> ARE YOU GLAD, INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
YEAH.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HANG ON, SHIPPO, I'LL GIVE
YOU A HAND.
>> DEMONS ARE RUNNING RAMPANT IN
MANY VILLAGES LIKE THIS ONE.
I'M GLAD THAT SHINTARO AND THE
OTHERS ARE ALL RIGHT.
BUT INUYASHA, YOU LOOK SO
TROUBLED.
WE LEFT MOUNT HAKUREI SO
QUICKLY IN PURSUIT OF NARAKU.
BUT I WONDER IF THAT WAS THE
BEST THING FOR INUYASHA.
WHAT HE REALLY WANTED, I THINK,
WAS TO STAY AND SEARCH FOR
KIKYO.
>> SUCH A FRIGHTENING IDEA.
COULD THE RUMORS BE TRUE?
>> IT'S SAID THAT MOUNT HAKUREI
COLLAPSED AWAY IN ONE NIGHT.
>> I SURE HOPE NOTHING BAD COMES
OF IT.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
[SCREAMING]
>> AAH!
>> THAT DEMONIC AURA.
>> DAMN IT!
>> INUYASHA, WAIT!
>> HORRIBLE.
>> AND THIS IS THE THIRD
VILLAGE.
>> I'M ONLY CATCHING THE SCENT
OF WEAKER DEMONS.
>> THIS MUST BE THE WORK OF
DEMONS WHICH ESCAPED FROM
MOUNT HAKUREI WHEN THE BARRIER
COLLAPSED.
YOU AGREE, INUYASHA?
>> DAMN, THIS IS AWFUL!
I THOUGHT THAT WE'D MADE
PROGRESS, FORCING NARAKU OUT
OF HIDING.
BUT THIS IS EVEN WORSE THAN
BEFORE!
ON TOP OF THAT, KIKYO WAS
KILLED.
>> HERE, THESE ARE FOR THE
GRAVES.
>> THANKS, BUT WE HAVE ENOUGH
NOW.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> HUH?
>> IT WOULD SEEM THERE'S BEEN
A TRAGEDY.
PLEASE, ALLOW ME TO HELP.
>> HUH?
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
>> SO, YOU CAME FROM THE AREA OF
MOUNT HAKUREI?
>> YES, I'VE BEEN ON A
PILGRIMAGE, TRAVELING AROUND
THESE LANDS.
I HEARD THAT MOUNT HAKUREI, THE
SACRED MOUNTAIN, HAD COLLAPSED,
AND THAT AN EVIL AURA WAS
SPREADING SOUTH.
>> I SEE.
>> ODDLY ENOUGH, IT'S EXACTLY AS
THAT PRIESTESS SAID.
>> HUH?
>> PRIESTESS?
>> IT WAS TWO DAYS AGO.
AN INJURED PRIESTESS WASHED UP
ON A RIVERBANK NEAR A VILLAGE ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF THE MOUNTAINS.
SHE MUMBLED ABOUT BEING WOUNDED
BY NARAKU.
THEN SHE SAID THAT SHE HAD TO GO
AFTER THIS NARAKU FELLOW.
>> IT HAS TO BE KIKYO.
THERE'S NO DOUBT.
SO SHE DID SURVIVE.
>> KIKYO!
>> HOWEVER, HER INJURIES WERE SO
SERIOUS, SHE MAY HAVE ALREADY
DIED FROM THEM.
>> HUH?
>> GO, INUYASHA.
>> KAGOME?
>> BUT, KAGOME--
>> THIS IS NO TIME TO HESITATE.
NOW HURRY.
KIKYO MUST BE WAITING.
>> YES.
FORGIVE ME.
>> ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS,
KAGOME?
>> IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
>> FORGIVE ME, KAGOME.
I HAVE TO MAKE SURE THIS TIME
IF KIKYO IS DEAD OR ALIVE.
OTHERWISE I WON'T BE ABLE TO
GO ON.
>> INUYASHA HASN'T RETURNED.
>> WELL, LET'S KEEP GOING.
INUYASHA WILL UNDOUBTEDLY PICK
UP KAGOME'S SCENT AND FIND US
THAT WAY.
>> I GUESS.
>> OH, HE'S RIGHT!
[HORSE NEIGHS]
>> HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, YOU 3!
DON'T MOVE.
YOU ALL LOOK SUSPICIOUS.
>> SUSPICIOUS?
MAYBE HE MEANS YOUR CLOTHING,
KAGOME.
>> THERE HAVE BEEN MANY STRANGE
HAPPENINGS IN THIS VICINITY
LATELY, SO WE HAVE BEEN
ORDERED TO DETAIN ALL
SUSPICIOUS-LOOKING TRAVELERS.
NOW COME!
>> UH...
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE CAN EASILY DEFEAT THEM AND
ESCAPE.
>> COME, COME, MY DEAR SANGO.
DON'T START TALKING LIKE
INUYASHA.
BESIDES, JUST LOOK AT THEM.
THEY'RE ORDINARY HUMANS, IF YOU
ASK ME.
WE CAN ESCAPE ANY TIME WE
CHOOSE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TWO TALKING
ABOUT OVER THERE?
GET THE ROPE AND TIE THEM UP!
>> OH, NO, THIS IS BAD!
>> [MEWS]
>> WE HAVE TO FIND INUYASHA AND
BRING HIM BACK.
LET'S GO, KIRARA.
>> PLEASE HAVE MERCY ON ME!
I'VE DONE NOTHING WRONG!
I HAVE ALL THE PROPER TRAVEL
DOCUMENTS IN MY POCKET.
>> KILL HIM.
>> YES, MY LADY.
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> WILL WE ALL BE KILLED?
>> THAT WASN'T MUCH OF A
HEARING, WAS IT?
>> HOW TERRIBLE!
>> I MUST SAY, THIS IS VERY
DISQUIETING.
>> SHE'S HERE.
>> HUH?
>> KAGOME!
>> COME WITH US IMMEDIATELY,
GIRL.
MY LADY COMMANDS IT.
>> JUST ME?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> I HAVE NO USE FOR THE OTHERS.
KILL THEM.
>> HYAH!
>> MIROKU!
SANGO!
>> INUYASHA!
WHERE ARE YOU?
INUYASHA!
HUH?
>> [ROARING]
>> AAH!
>> UNH!
HUH?
>> NOW THAT KIKYO IS DEAD, IT
SEEMS YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE ABLE
TO SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS.
>> HUH?
THE PRIEST FROM YESTERDAY!
[GASPS]
>> HONESTLY, I'VE HAD IT.
THAT BASTARD MAKES ME LOOK AFTER
THE STUPID INFANT.
>> KAGURA!
THEN THIS PRIEST...
>> DON'T YOU SEE?
I WAS CONTROLLING HIM WITH MY
DANCE OF THE DEAD.
>> THEN THE STORY ABOUT KIKYO
BEING ALIVE WAS A LIE.
>> NO ONE WILL COME TO SAVE YOU.
THE MONK AND DEMON-SLAYER WILL
BE KILLED BY THE CASTLE
SOLDIERS.
>> THE WOMAN ISN'T THE ONE
ACTUALLY SPEAKING.
>> INUYASHA WILL NOT COME.
INUYASHA IS COMPLETELY OBSESSED
WITH FINDING KIKYO.
>> THIS INFANT IS...
NARAKU'S INCARNATION!
>> THIS BABY IS AN INCARNATION
OF NARAKU, BORN AT
MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> JUST WHAT DO YOU INTEND TO DO
WITH ME?
>> I TOLD YOU.
YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE LEFT WHO
CAN SEE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
I HAVE NEED OF YOUR EYES.
>> [GASPS]
>> NOW RESIGN YOURSELF TO DEATH!
>> AAH!
>> UNH!
>> HUH?
A HIDDEN WEAPON?
>> UNH!
UHH!
>> THAT DAMNABLE WITCH!
HOW DARE SHE!
DON'T LET THOSE TWO GET AWAY!
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> THANKS, SANGO.
>> AAH!
>> UNH!
>> OHH...
>> I'M TAKING THESE BACK.
>> OH!
>> UNH!
UHH...
>> AAH!
QUICK, RUN AWAY!
>> HOLD IT!
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
>> UNH!
>> OH!
>> OUT OF THE WAY!
THESE GUYS AREN'T ANY REAL
CHALLENGE.
>> YES.
BUT, SANGO, DON'T FORGET THAT
THESE MEN ARE ONLY FOLLOWING
ORDERS FROM SOMEONE HIGHER UP.
WE CAN HARDLY START KILLING
THEM.
AND BESIDES, WE'RE OUTNUMBERED.
THIS MAY TAKE A LITTLE BIT
OF TIME.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT, BUT THEY
TOOK KAGOME AND SHE NEEDS
OUR HELP.
WE HAVE TO HURRY.
>> [YELLING]
>> KAGOME, I WILL MAKE GOOD USE
OF YOUR EYES.
KAGURA, I WANT YOU TO UNTIE HER
ROPES NOW.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> AH!
AAH!
NO!
>> WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF?
DO YOU THINK I'LL TAKE YOUR
EYES AND THEN PERHAPS EAT YOU?
>> [BREATHING HARD]
[GASPING]
>> WHAT IS IT ABOUT THIS GIRL'S
SOUL?
I CAN FIND NO DARKNESS.
THAT CANNOT BE.
WITH EVERY HUMAN, THERE IS
ALWAYS SOME DARKNESS IN
THEIR SOUL.
PERHAPS ANGER, HATRED, OR...
>> [GASPS]
WHAT IS...THIS TERRIBLE
FEELING?
IT'S LIKE HE'S GROPING AROUND
INSIDE MY HEART.
HELP ME!
HELP ME, INUYASHA!
INUYASHA ISN'T...ISN'T COMING
TO RESCUE ME.
>> KAGOME, I'M OK.
>> INUYASHA ISN'T COMING.
HE'S STILL SEARCHING FOR KIKYO.
>> FORGIVE ME.
>> INUYASHA ISN'T GOING TO COME
AND SAVE ME.
INUYASHA!
>> I FOUND IT!
I FINALLY GRASP THE DARKNESS IN
YOUR HEART, KAGOME.
YOU CAN'T GET AWAY FROM ME NOW.
NOW HOLD ME TIGHTLY.
LET OUR SOULS UNITE AND BECOME
MY EYES.
>> INUYASHA...
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]