>> WIND SCAR!
I USED THE TETSEIGA TO BREAK
THROUGH NARAKU'S BARRIER...
AND I ALMOST HAD HIM, BUT HE
ABANDONED HIS CASTLE AND
DISAPPEARED WITHOUT A TRACE.
NARAKU HAD A COMPLETELY
VANISHED.
THE DEMON LEFT BEHIND IN THE
CASTLE TOLD US NARAKU HAD GONE
SOMEWHERE THAT NO ONE COULD
TOUCH HIM.
COULD SUCH A PLACE REALLY EXIST?
HE MUST'VE BEEN CONFIDENT THAT
HE WOULDN'T BE FOUND TO SAY
SUCH A THING TO HIS DEMON
INCARNATION.
>> I WILL DEVOUR YOU WHOLE,
SWORD AND ALL!
>> HUH!
SIZE ISN'T ALL THAT COUNTS, BIG
GUY!
WAIT AND SEE!
UP AND OVER!
>> [GROWLING]
>> [YELLS]
>> KOUGA!
>> AYAME!
>> KOUGA, AYAME!
>> [GASPS]
>> HE NEVER STOOD A CHANCE.
>> WE CAN'T SURRENDER.
THIS TIME I WILL FIND HIM AND
DESTROY HIM FOR GOOD.
WHERE DID YOU GET TO, NARAKU?
[METAL CLANKING]
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> YES, I SENSED IT, TOO.
THE DEMONIC AURA HAS BEEN
GETTING STRONGER AND STRONGER.
>> A DEMON?
>> HANG ON, INUYASHA.
[BELLS RINGING]
>> SHOW YOURSELF, APPARITION!
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
[BELLS RINGING]
THERE YOU ARE.
>> [SQUEALING]
YOU SHALL DIE, YOU WEASEL DEMON!
[GROANING]
>> [HISSING]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> [GASPS]
>> YOU SHOULDN'T GO WANDERING
ABOUT LIKE THIS, OLD WOMAN.
GO HOME WHERE IT IS SAFE AND
WARM.
>> YOU HAVE DOG EARS.
ANOTHER NEW DEMON?
OFF WITH YOU, DEMON!
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING?
THAT IS SOME WAY TO SHOW YOUR
GRATITUDE!
>> THAT IS QUITE ENOUGH.
>> DON'T EVEN TRY TO STOP ME.
>> THAT'S IT, MONK.
HOLD HIM RIGHT THERE.
OFF WITH YOU, DEMON!
>> [COUGHING]
>> DEMONS ARE ON THE RISE?
>> THAT EXPLAINS THE DEMONIC
AURA.
>> DEMONIC AURA?
>> WE JOURNEY AROUND THE
COUNTRYSIDE SLAYING DEMONS.
>> HMM, SO WE ARE COMRADES.
ANYWAY, AS I WAS TELLING YOU,
THERE HAS BEEN A SUDDEN
INCREASE IN DEMONS, WHICH IS WHY
I CAME OUT OF RETIREMENT.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE DONE THE
WORLD A FAVOR AND STAYED
RETIRED, OLD WOMAN.
>> PERHAPS YOU NEED ANOTHER
LESSON.
>> CALM DOWN, MADAM EXORCIST.
>> HUH?
>> YOU WOULDN'T KNOW THE REASON
FOR THE INCREASE IN DEMONS,
WOULD YOU?
>> I AM QUITE SURE IT IS BECAUSE
OF THE CURSE.
>> WHAT CURSE?
>> OF THE DEMON'S HEAD CASTLE.
>> DEMON'S HEAD CASTLE?
>> IT PROBABLY HAS A PROPER
NAME, BUT EVERYONE CALLS IT THE
DEMON'S HEAD CASTLE.
IT IS SAID THAT THE HEAD OF A
DEMON DESTROYED BY AN ANCESTOR
WAS BURIED TO WARD OFF EVIL
SPIRITS, AND THE CASTLE WAS
BUILT OVER IT.
>> DON'T TELL ME YOU ACTUALLY
BELIEVE THE OLD HAG?
>> HMM!
>> FOR SOME STRANGE REASON, THE
DEMON HAS COME OUT OF HIDING
LATELY AND HAS STARTED
TORMENTING PEOPLE AGAIN, AND NO
AMOUNT OF EXORCISM HAS WORKED.
NOW THEN, FOLLOW ME.
>> FOLLOW YOU?
WHERE TO?
>> TO DEMON'S HEAD CASTLE, WHERE
ELSE?
DIDN'T YOU SAY YOU YOUNGSTERS
WERE DEMON SLAYERS?
>> WHAT'LL WE DO?
>> WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS!
>> BUT SINCE WE ALREADY KNOW THE
STORY--
>> FINDING NARAKU IS TOP
PRIORITY.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
>> I UNDERSTAND THE REWARD IS
TREMENDOUS.
>> WHO NEEDS A REWARD?
HMM--HUH?
>> WELL, WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR
THEN?
>> WE SPLIT THE EARNINGS EVENLY.
>> MAN!
>> [HISSING]
>> [GASP]
>> SPYING ON ME?
>> NO.
MY LORD, PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I DID NOT SEE ANYTHING, NOTHING
AT ALL!
MY LORD!
[SCREAMING]
>> I SEE.
>> IN ANY CASE, OUR LORD HAS
BEEN ACTING STRANGE IN RECENT
DAYS; HE LOCKS HIMSELF UP IN HIS
ROOM AND REFUSES TO LEAVE.
>> HEY, INUYASHA, DON'T YOU FIND
THIS CASTLE SORT OF CREEPY?
>> YEAH, THAT FIELD WAS NOTHING
COMPARED TO THIS PLACE.
THIS MUST BE THE CENTER OF THE
DEMONIC AURA.
>> DEFINITELY A DEMONIC AURA...
>> ...SURROUNDING
THE ENTIRE CASTLE.
>> HMM?
WHAT IS THE REASON BEHIND THE
GLUM FACES, AND WHAT ARE YOU ALL
MUMBLING ABOUT BACK THERE?
>> EVERYONE SENSES THE DEMONIC
AURA, SO WE'RE UNEASY.
>> DEMONIC AURA?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> MADAM EXORCIST, DON'T YOU
FEEL OR SENSE ANYTHING UNUSUAL
HERE AT THE CASTLE?
>> LIKE WHAT.
>> IS THIS WOMAN FOR REAL?
>> IT'S ALL IN YOUR IMAGINATION.
OR PERHAPS YOU'RE ALL FEELING
FRIGHTENED?
YOU'RE SO YOUNG--ABSOLUTELY
HOPELESS.
>> DOES ANYONE ELSE GET THE
FEELING THAT SHE'S A FAKE?
>> YEAH, EVEN I CAN SENSE THE
DEMONIC AURA.
HUH?
>> ANOTHER BODY.
THAT IS THE SEVENTH VICTIM.
THE LORD SLAYS EVERY VASSAL WHO
MADE THE CHOICE TO APPROACH HIS
ROOM.
>> DO YOU THINK HIS ERRATIC
BEHAVIOR IS CAUSED BY THE
DEMON'S CURSE?
>> MOST LIKELY.
THE DEMON APPEARS AFTER DARK HAS
FALLEN.
UNTIL THEN, PLEASE COME AND REST
INSIDE.
>> ONE, TWO, 3.
ONE, TWO, 3.
[SIGHS]
NOW LISTEN UP--YOU MUST BE
PREPARED.
>> YOU SURE GOT SPUNK, OLD
WOMAN.
>> [TO HERSELF] I'LL SAY,
SHE'S AMAZING IN THIS
DEMONIC AURA.
>> THE DEMONIC AURA HERE IS
UNSETTLING, EVEN FOR THOSE AS
EXPERIENCED AS WE.
LET'S FINISH THIS UP AND GET OUT
OF HERE QUICKLY.
>> I AGREE.
>> HMM?
>> YOU ARE THE ONES WHO HAVE
COME TO SLAY THE DEMON?
PLEASE, BE CAREFUL...
AND DO WHATEVER IT TAKES TO SAVE
MY FATHER.
>> YOUR FATHER?
>> YOU'RE THE PRINCESS OF THIS
CASTLE?
>> MANY MONKS AND PRIESTESSES
HAVE ATTEMPTED TO EXORCISE THE
DEMON BUT HAVE FAILED EACH TIME.
THEY PAID WITH THEIR VERY LIVES.
>> REST ASSURED, MY DEAR
PRINCESS.
I SHALL STAND FIRM HERE AND
CONDUCT THE EXORCISM NO MATTER
HOW MANY DAYS AND NIGHTS IT
REQUIRES.
>> [TO HERSELF] WEREN'T YOU
JUST SAYING WE
SHOULD FINISH THIS UP QUICKLY
AND GET OUT OF HERE?
>> THE DEMON!
THE DEMON HAS RETURNED!
>> DON'T WORRY, PRINCESS.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS!
>> [SNARLING]
>> THE DEMON HEAD!
>> [GROWLING]
>> I'LL GO.
KIRARA!
I'LL DESTROY IT IN ONE SHOT!
>> SANGO'S STRONG, BUT DOESN'T
SHE LOOK MORE INTENSE THAN
USUAL?
>> YEAH, THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> [GROWLING]
>> HERE I COME!
>> IT WENT THROUGH IT!
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> MOVE, SANGO!
WIND SCAR!
>> [CHOKING]
>> AND THAT, MY FRIENDS, IS HOW
IT IS DONE.
>> INUYASHA, UP THERE!
>> WHAT IS GOING ON?
[TO HIMSELF] HUH, HOW CAN THAT
BE?
I HIT IT SQUARE ON WITH MY WIND
SCAR AND IT HARDLY FLINCHED.
WAIT, IS THAT DEMON HEAD REAL?
>> [SNARLING]
>> YOU ARE A SUCKER FOR
PUNISHMENT.
WIND SCAR!
>> [CHOKING]
>> DID I GET HIM?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
>> WAIT, INUYASHA.
>> WHY SHOULD I?
IF MY WIND SCAR DIDN'T WORK HOW
DO YOU EXPECT TO DESTROY IT?
>> NO WEAPON WILL WORK ON THAT.
>> WHA...
MIROKU?
>> SACRED...!
>> [GROANING]
>> IT'S GONE.
>> PRINCESS, THE DEMON HAS
VANISHED.
>> JUST AS I THOUGHT.
THAT DEMON WAS NO MORE THAN AN
ILLUSION.
>> IT WASN'T REAL?
>> DOES THAT MEAN THE DEMON HEAD
WILL APPEAR AGAIN TOMORROW
NIGHT?
>> YES, IT WILL, BECAUSE IT IS
MAKE-BELIEVE, AN ILLUSION TO
DIVERT EVERYONE'S ATTENTION FROM
THE REAL DEMON.
>> SO THAT MEANS THE REAL DEMON
MUST BE HIDING SOMEWHERE IN
THIS CASTLE.
>> PROBABLY.
THE DEMONIC AURA HASN'T SUBSIDED
AT ALL.
>> HMM.
DEMONIC AURA, HUH?
MM, MM, MM.
WELL, I DON'T SENSE ANYTHING AT
ALL.
>> HOW ODD.
>> [TO HERSELF] SOME EXORCIST
YOU ARE.
>> DIDN'T YOU SAY THAT THE LORD
HAS BECOME DERANGED?
>> YES, THAT IS CORRECT.
>> ARE YOU SURE IT'S A DEMON'S
CURSE AND NOT SIMPLY A CASE OF
HIM BEING POSSESSED?
[THUNDER AND HOWLING WIND]
>> IF YOU ARE NOTICED YOU WILL
BE KILLED!
>> IF THAT HAPPENS, I'LL FIGHT
BACK.
>> DON'T BE SO HASTY; HE IS THE
LORD OF THE CASTLE.
>> WELL, MIROKU, IS IT A DEMON?
>> NO, HE IS DEFINITELY HUMAN.
AND...
>> HUH?
WHAT?
>> THERE IS NO WAY THE DEMONIC
AURA SURROUNDING THE CASTLE IS
COMING FROM THE LORD.
DEFINITELY NOT.
>> [GROANING]
>> [COUGHING]
>> WELL, NOW, DON'T YOU FEEL A
LITTLE BETTER?
>> NOT IN THE LEAST.
[COUGHING]
>> WHAT?
NOT EVEN A LITTLE?
>> DID IT WORK ON YOU, KIRARA?
>> WELL?
NOW THAT IS STRANGE.
THIS IS A VERY SPECIAL BLEND OF
MY PURIFICATION SALT; MOST
DEMONS SUCCUMB TO IT AT ONCE.
>> YOU ARE SUCH A FAKE.
AS IF THAT STUFF WOULD WORK.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
SHALL I GIVE YOU A SHOT OF IT!?
>> OVER HERE, OVER HERE!
>> HOLD IT!
WAIT, I SAY!.
>> NO WAY!
>> DEMON.
>> SIT!
>> WHAT?
[GROANS]
>> WILL YOU TWO GIVE IT A REST
ALREADY?
>> MY FATHER COULD BE THE
DEMON!?
>> YES, PRINCESS.
ACCORDING TO THE MONK, YOUR
FATHER IS MERELY POSSESSED AND
THE DEMON HIMSELF COULD BE
LOCATED ANYWHERE IN THE CASTLE.
>> EXCUSE ME, MONK, THE PRINCESS
HAS REQUESTED YOUR PRESENCE.
>> WHO, ME?
>> HOLD ON, YOU'RE NOT GOING
ALONE ARE YOU?
>> FEAR NOT, MY DEAR SANGO.
IT IS TRUE THAT THE PRINCESS IS
BEAUTIFUL, BUT IT IS OF NO
MATTER.
MY HEART BELONGS TO YOU.
>> THAT'S HARDLY THE ISSUE HERE.
I MEANT THAT IT'S TOO DANGEROUS
TO GO ALONE SINCE THE DEMON
COULD SHOW UP AGAIN ANY MOMENT
NOW.
>> IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN, THEN
DON'T WORRY.
MIROKU'S STRONG ENOUGH TO TAKE
CARE OF HIMSELF.
WHAT'S WITH THE GLARE?
>> [TO HERSELF] WELL, DUH!
>> YOU STILL HAVE MUCH TO STUDY
IN THE LESSONS OF LIFE.
>> WHAT!?
YOU FAKE EXORCIST!
>> WELL, I'M NOT SURE ABOUT HER
ABILITY AS AN EXORCIST, BUT SHE
IS PRETTY SHARP AS A WOMAN.
>> THANKS A LOT, TRAITOR.
>> NOW THEN.
>> MONK.
>> YES.
>> TAKE THIS PURIFICATION
SALT--JUST ONE PACKET--MERELY
AS A PRECAUTION.
>> THANK YOU.
I AM MUCH OBLIGED.
IT IS A VERY LONG STAIRWAY.
>> YOU'VE PROBABLY HEARD THIS
ALREADY: THE BURIAL SITE OF THE
DEMON HEAD IS DOWN BELOW.
>> COULD YOU TELL ME MORE?
>> THE HEAD OF A CONQUERED DEMON
IS BURIED BENEATH THIS CASTLE.
I FELT STRANGELY COMPELLED TO
SHOW IT TO YOU, MONK.
>> I HEARD THAT THE DEMON HEAD
WAS BURIED HERE TO WARD OFF
EVIL.
>> YES, THAT IS TRUE.
BUT UNTIL RECENTLY IT HAS NOT
BEEN A PROBLEM.
THEN THE BURIAL SITE WAS
UNCOVERED AND THE DEMON ESCAPED.
AND AS YOU CAN SEE, DOWN IN THIS
HOLE...
>> HUH!
HUMAN BONES!
>> HUMAN BONES!
>> THESE ARE THE SKELETONS OF
THE MONKS AND PRIESTESSES WHO
FAILED TO SLAY THE DEMON.
>> THIS IS HORRIFIC.
>> THE DEMON THAT OCCUPIED THIS
CASTLE CRAVED HUMANS LIKE THEM
AND DRAINED THEM OF THEIR
SPIRITUAL POWERS, LEAVING ONLY
THEIR BONES.
>> I SEE.
THAT'S WHY IT WANTS ME HERE.
>> EXACTLY, HMM.
>> HUH?
>> TO ABSORB YOUR SPIRITUAL
POWERS.
>> [YAWNS]
I WONDER WHAT IS TAKING MIROKU
SO DAMN LONG.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S SURE LATE; I WONDER WHAT HE
IS DOING.
>> KNOWING THAT LECHER AND
CONSIDERING HOW LONG HE'S BEEN
WITH THE PRINCESS, RIGHT ABOUT
NOW HE'S--
>> [GROANING]
>> UH...
>> NAH, NOT EVEN MIROKU WOULD DO
ANYTHING IN THIS DEMONIC AURA.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
HE'S A PERVERT!
A LITTLE THING LIKE THIS
WOULDN'T STOP HIM.
I CAN JUST PICTURE HIM.
AND BELIEVE ME, IT'S NOT THE
DEMONIC AURA HE'S FEELING.
>> INUYASHA, SIT!
>> WOULD YOU STOP DOING THAT?
>> YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW THE
MEANING OF BEING TACTFUL.
>> LIKE I SAID, NOT ENOUGH
TRAINING.
>> HEY, SANGO, WHAT DO YOU SAY
YOU AND I GO AND LOOK FOR HIM?
>> NO, THANK YOU.
I DON'T WANT TO INTERRUPT HIM.
>> [TO HERSELF] YES, YOU DO!
>> IT'S HERE.
>> [GROANING]
>> MY LORD!
>> PLEASE, STOP THIS!
>> [GROWLING]
[GROANING]
>> [ALL GASPING]
>> [GROANING]
>> THE LORD HAS BECOME A DEMON!
>> NO, MY LORD!
>> LET HIM GO.
SO, THIS IS THE TRUE FORM OF THE
DEMON.
>> YOU'RE THE DEMON.
>> [CHUCKLES]
A LITTLE TOO LATE, I'M AFRAID.
YOU HAVE INHALED THE DEMONIC
AURA AND YOUR BODY IS FEELING
LIMP.
>> [GROANING]
HUH?
NO!
>> [IN DEMONIC VOICE] DAMN YOU!
>> I MADE SURE I BROUGHT THE
EXORCIST'S PURIFICATION SALTS;
ADDING MY SPIRITUAL POWER MADE
IT WORK.
[TO HIMSELF] I'M IN TROUBLE--
THIS DEMON IS
POWERFUL AND THIS DEMONIC AURA
HAS LEFT ME PARALYZED.
>> [LAUGHTER]
MONK, THERE IS NO HELP
FORTHCOMING.
BESIDES, THAT HALF-DEMON IS
PROBABLY FIGHTING THE LORD BACK
AT THE CASTLE.
I USED MY DARK MAGIC TO
MANIPULATE THAT FOOLISH PUPPET
LORD.
[DEMONIC LAUGHTER]
>> WHAT!?
INUYASHA, HELP ME!
>> [CRYING]
>> HOPE YOU'RE PREPARED FOR YOUR
FUNERAL, DEMON.
>> [GROWLING]
>> [CHUCKLES]
ONE STRIKE IS ALL IT'LL TAKE.
>> [GROWLING]
[FEMALE SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> WHAT'LL WE DO, KAGOME?
MIROKU HASN'T COME BACK SINCE HE
WENT UNDERGROUND WITH THE
PRINCESS, AND SANGO IS STILL SO
JEALOUS SHE'S BASICALLY
USELESS!
YOU AND I ARE THE ONLY ONES ABLE
TO SET UP A PREVIEW FOR THE
NEXT EPISODE!
KAGOME!
>> HUH?
WHAT IS IT, SHIPPO?
>> YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
HELPING, NOT SLEEPING!
>> I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF AFTER
SEEING THE PRINCESS HAVING SUCH
A GOOD SLEEP.
>> NEXT TIME, "SECRET OF THE
POSSESSED PRINCESS."
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE, ANYWAY?