- WH-WHAT IS IT?
IS SOMETHING ON FIRE?
- NO, THEY'RE JUST
SLAYING DEMONS.
- AND WHAT STINKS?
- WHAT'S ALL THE SMOKE FOR?
- GOT EVERYTHING READY?
MOOR IT THIS WAY.
- COULDN'T WE USE A MOUSETRAP?
SANGO, YOU ALMOST DONE?
- [GROANING]
- IS THIS ONE OF THE DEMONS
BEING DESTROYED BY THE SMOKE?
- INUYASHA JUST HAS
A VERY SENSITIVE NOSE.
- HMM?
- [MURMURING]
- MM-HMM.
WHAT A BEAUTY.
- HEY, MIROKU,
WHERE YOU GOING?
- IT'S COMING. GET BACK!
- AAH!
[CROWD GASPING]
[ROAR]
[GASPING]
- EVERYTHING'S OK NOW, KAGOME.
- ARE YOU STILL
FEELING SICK, INUYASHA?
HUH? WHERE'S MIROKU?
- HE FOLLOWED
AFTER SOME STRANGE WOMAN.
- HUH?
- HE DID?
WHILE WE WERE SLAYING DEMONS?
- SHE WAS REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
HE PROBABLY
GAVE HER THE LINE
ABOUT HAVING TO HAVE
HIS FIRSTBORN CHILD.
- WH-WHAT?
HAVE HIS CHILD?
- I SEE. SO YOU'RE
A PRINCESS FROM A VERY
PROMINENT CLAN, THEN.
- I WAS.
MY CLAN HAD BEEN
DECIMATED BY WAR,
AND I AM THE SOLE SURVIVOR
OF MY HOUSE.
SO IN ORDER
TO RESTORE MY FAMILY,
I WISH TO BEAR THE CHILD
OF A STRONG LORD.
- SO YOU SOUGHT ME OUT.
HMM, YOU HAVE GREAT TASTE.
- WILL YOU DO ME THE HONOR?
- [SIGH]
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN THIS WAS
ALL FAR TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
[GRUNTING]
- UNH!
HIYAH!
- [GASP]
A GIANT MANTIS!
SO YOU DISGUISED YOURSELF
AS A WOMAN.
- I DEVOURED THE INNARDS
OF THE REAL PRINCESS.
- UHH!
UHH! UNH!
YOU PICKED THE WRONG PERSON
FOR YOUR NEXT VICTIM!
YAH!
WIND TUNNEL!
- [LAUGHING]
- [GASP]
HMM! DAMN,
MY WIND TUNNEL'S INJURED.
TELL ME, INUYASHA.
IS IT MY IMAGINATION,
OR HAVE THE GIRLS
BEEN STARING AT ME
QUITE COLDLY?
- WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S FROM
ALL THE WOMANIZING.
- HMM?
- WHAT DO YOU EXPECT, MIROKU?
THEY THINK YOU'RE
A PHILANDERING CREEP.
- I'VE BEEN MISUNDERSTOOD.
YOU MAY NOT BELIEVE WHAT
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU, BUT...
- YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
- SPARE US THE LIES.
- YOU COULD AT LEAST GIVE ME
A CHANCE TO EXPLAIN MYSELF.
UNH.
DAMN, IT STILL HURTS.
THAT CONNIVING GIANT MANTIS
MADE MY WIND TUNNEL SPREAD.
FATHER! FATHER!
- NO! DON'T GO
TOWARDS HIM, MIROKU!
- FATHER! FATHER!
- UNH!
- LET ME GO, MUSHIN!
- YOU WOULD BE PULLED
INTO YOUR FATHER'S
WIND TUNNEL, TOO, IF YOU GO.
- HUH?
FATHER! NO!
[PANTING]
- HE WENT OUT BEFORE DAWN.
YOU'RE SURE?
- YES. THE MONK SAID
HE WAS GOING ON A LONG JOURNEY,
AND HE ASKED ME
TO WISH YOU WELL.
- THAT STUPID MIROKU.
ALWAYS RUNNING OFF
AND DOING THINGS ON HIS OWN.
- MY FATHER WAS DRAWN
INTO HIS OWN WIND TUNNEL,
AND HE DISAPPEARED
WITHOUT A TRACE.
I'M AFRAID I'LL PROBABLY
END UP DYING THAT WAY AS WELL.
- MIROKU, WE FOUND A SPOT.
I CAN SEE IT FROM HERE.
- HMM.
- [PANTING]
WHERE DID THIS GIANT HOLE
COME FROM ANYWAY?
- HMM. THIS?
THIS IS MY FATHER'S GRAVE.
MUSHIN, ARE YOU THERE?
- [SNORING]
- IT'S MIROKU.
UH! DRUNK AGAIN AS USUAL. UH!
- HMM?
- WAKE UP,
YOU STINKING DRUNKARD.
- UHH...
MIROKU, I'M SURPRISED
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
- YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO LIVE VERY LONG
IF YOU KEEP DRINKING
THE WAY YOU DO.
- DID YOU COME HERE
TO LECTURE ME?
- NO. A GIANT MANTIS
NICKED THE SIDES
OF MY WIND TUNNEL.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD REPAIR IT.
- HMM.
HMM. HMM.
TOO LATE.
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE TONIGHT.
RELAX.
I'M JUST KIDDING AROUND.
[HICCUP]
[GROAN]
- LOOK, YOU WANT
TO GET SUCKED IN?
- NOW, NOW. CALM DOWN.
I'LL STITCH YOU UP,
BUT I'M WARNING YOU.
YOU MUST KEEP
THE WIND TUNNEL COVERED UP
AND NOT EXPOSE IT
OR TRY TO USE IT
UNTIL IT IS COMPLETELY HEALED.
- AND WHAT HAPPENS IF I DO?
- THE WIND TUNNEL
WILL SPREAD FROM THE NICK
AND WILL EVENTUALLY
CONSUME YOU ENTIRELY.
I WILL NO LONGER BE ABLE
TO HELP YOU THEN, YOUNG MAN.
- NOW, THEN. UNH.
I WILL START GATHERING
MY MEDICINAL HERBS.
GO AND PURIFY YOURSELF.
GOD KNOWS YOU NEED IT.
- HMM. SO THAT
DRUNKEN OLD MAN MUSHIN
IS THE HIGH MONK
WHO RAISED YOU?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
HE TAUGHT ME EVERYTHING I KNOW.
THE GOOD AND THE BAD.
- HE'S A LITTLE ROUGH
AROUND THE EDGES,
THAT'S FOR SURE,
BUT HE SEEMS KINDHEARTED.
- HMM. I GUESS SO.
- I'M SURPRISED MIROKU
IS SO WORRIED
OVER A LITTLE NICK
LIKE THAT,
BUT CONSIDERING
THE TRAGEDY IN HIS LIFE,
I CAN'T BLAME HIM
FOR BEING UPSET.
- I WONDER WHY MIROKU
TOOK OFF ON US YESTERDAY
WITHOUT A WORD TO ANYONE.
- WELL, MAYBE
IT'S BECAUSE BOTH OF YOU
SHOT HIM SUCH DIRTY LOOKS.
- HMM?
- HUH. DON'T TRY AND TELL ME
THAT WE HURT HIS FEELINGS.
HE'S NOT EXACTLY SENSITIVE.
- UH, WELL, MASTER INUYASHA.
- WELL, WELL, MYOGA.
YOU'RE BACK.
- YES. I RETURNED LATE
LAST NIGHT,
AND WHEN I CAME IN,
I NOTICED THAT THE MONK
WAS ACTING STRANGELY.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- HE KEPT STARING
AT HIS RIGHT HAND--
THE ONE WITH THE WIND TUNNEL--
AND HE SEEMED
VERY DEEP IN THOUGHT.
HE DIDN'T SAY
WHAT WAS BOTHERING HIM.
- HUH? INUYASHA,
LET'S GO FIND MIROKU.
- WHY? YOU DON'T THINK
SOMETHING'S HAPPENED
TO HIM, DO YOU?
- HMM. WELL, YES,
BUT WE'RE NOT SURE WHAT.
- SO, HOW DO YOU EXPECT US
TO GO AND FIND HIM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- JUST LEAVE HIM.
FINDING THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
IS MORE IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO YOU, MIROKU?
- HMM.
IT'S THE MIDDLE
OF THE AFTERNOON.
WHY IS IT SUDDENLY
SO DARK OUTSIDE?
HMM? UHH!
WH-WHO ARE YOU?
UHH!
- [SNORING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
- DID YOU DRINK YOUR MEDICINE?
- HMM? YES, BUT I'M STARTING
TO FEEL VERY GROGGY.
- SLEEP.
IT WILL BE OVER SOON.
- GLAD TO HEAR IT
BECAUSE I DON'T FEEL
LIKE DYING JUST YET.
MMM.
- [CHUCKLING]
I'LL EASE YOUR PAIN
SOON ENOUGH.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- WHAT WAS THAT NOISE?
- I DON'T LIKE
THE SOUNDS OF IT.
WHAT IS IT, INUYASHA?
[BUZZING]
- [GASP]
NARAKU'S INSECTS!
- HIRAIKOTSU! UNH!
THIS TIME, IT'S DEAD.
- WAIT! IF HE'S USING THEM
TO SPY ON US,
SOMETHING MUST BE HAPPENING
WITH MIROKU.
LET'S FOLLOW IT!
- OK. COME ON. WAIT FOR ME!
- HUH?
UNH!
[PANTING]
- OH. ARE YOU STILL AWAKE?
- YOU'RE NOT MUSHIN.
WHO ARE YOU?
- I AM A DEMON WORM CHARMER,
BUT I CAME ACROSS NARAKU,
AND HE PROMISED TO GIVE ME
A SACRED JEWEL SHARD
IF I KILLED YOU.
- UH, NARAKU? HUH?
- UNH!
- [CHUCKLING]
YOU CAN'T MOVE MUCH ANYMORE.
THE MEDICINE HAS NUMBED
YOUR ENTIRE BODY.
GO NOW IN PEACE!
- UNH!
UGH!
- MIROKU!
- QUICK, MY STAFF!
- UNH!
[GRUNTING]
- UH! KABOOM!
- [GRUMBLING]
YOU WON'T GET AWAY!
- HURRY. LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- I CAN'T GO ANY FASTER.
- OH, NO. LOOK!
THE DEMONS ARE GATHERING.
- [GASP]
- SAVE YOURSELF.
IF YOU STAY WITH ME,
YOU'LL ONLY DIE.
- UNH!
- UHH! UHH!
- MASTER MIROKU.
- JUST GO. I CAN KEEP THEM
AT BAY MYSELF
UNTIL THE MEDICINE
WEARS OFF, HACHI.
- B-B-BUT...
- JUST GO!
- OK.
- UNH.
[GRUNTING]
- MIROKU TALKS BIG,
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
HE CAN HANDLE
ALL THOSE DEMONS ALONE.
INUYASHA MUST BE CLOSE BY.
[BUZZING]
UHH!
AAH!
- THIS INSECT
IS OUR ONLY LEAD,
SO DON'T LOSE IT, OK?
- MM-HMM.
- AAH!
MORE POISONOUS BUGS!
- WHAT?
- HELP ME!
- AAH!
UNH!
- THAT'S HACHI!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
[BUZZING]
- TO THINK I'M GOING TO DIE
BECAUSE I LIKE TO FLIRT
WITH WOMEN.
IT'S JUST MY LUCK.
SO, THIS IS IT.
- SO MIROKU IS IN DANGER.
I KNEW IT.
- YES, AND HE DOESN'T HAVE
THE USE OF HIS WIND TUNNEL.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
- HIS HAND WAS INJURED
IN BATTLE.
THE SIDES OF IT GOT NICKED
WHEN HE TRIED TO SUCK IN
A GIANT MANTIS.
HE WENT TO THE HIGH PRIEST
MUSHIN TO GET IT FIXED,
THEN MUSHIN SAID IF HE
USED HIS WIND TUNNEL
BEFORE IT HEALED,
IT WOULD SPREAD AND KILL HIM.
OH! THERE'S
THE HIGH PRIEST'S TEMPLE!
AAH!
- GO STRAIGHT
THROUGH THEM, HACHI! YAH!
- AAH!
- YAH!
- UNH!
- I AIN'T GONNA WASTE MY TIME!
UNH! GET OUT OF THE WAY!
- I WILL ACCEPT MY DEATH
WITH GRACE.
I WILL FACE MY FOE
UNFLINCHINGLY,
AND I WILL DIE WITH HONOR.
I WON'T FIGHT WHEN IT'S FUTILE
LIKE INUYASHA WOULD.
HMM? HMM?
- MIROKU?
SO, THIS IS WHERE
YOU'VE BEEN HIDING,
AND YOU GOT YOURSELF
IN TROUBLE AGAIN.
- INUYASHA, YOU CAME.
- YOU COULD AT LEAST THANK ME
FOR SAVING YOUR SORRY BUTT.
- MIROKU!
MIROKU, WHY DID YOU LEAVE US
WITHOUT SAYING ANYTHING?
- YEAH. HOW COULD YOU?
WE WERE SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
- HAVE YOU BEEN INJURED, MIROKU?
- ALL OF THEM
CAME LOOKING FOR ME.
- WELL, INUYASHA,
SAY SOMETHING.
- HUMPH. I'M NOT INTO SPEECHES.
BESIDES, YOU ALREADY SAID
WHAT I WAS GONNA SAY.
- WHO GOES THERE?
HMM?
I WILL PUNISH ANYONE
WHO DARES TO DISTURB
THE PEACE OF MY TEMPLE.
- ARE YOU THE MONK
CALLED MUSHIN?
VERY INTERESTING.
YOU'RE BRAVE
FOR TAKING ME ON.
FIGHT ME IF YOU CAN.
- INUYASHA, I BEG YOU.
PLEASE, DON'T DESTROY HIM.
- [CHUCKLING]
THAT'S A VERY GOOD BOY, MIROKU.
I RAISED YOU WELL,
DIDN'T I?
- WHO REALLY CARES
IF YOU RAISED HIM?
YOUR DRINKING DAYS ARE OVER,
YOU OLD DRUNK!
- YAH!
- HUH? UNH!
- THE TETSUSAIGA'S
BEEN TRANSFORMED BACK.
- AAH! UGH!
UNH!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
- MY, MY. AREN'T WE LIVELY?
- UNH! AAH! UGH!
DAMN IT. WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I HAVE YOU BOUND
WITH MY SUTRA MAGIC,
SO I'M SURPRISED
YOU CAN STILL MOVE,
BUT YOU WON'T LAST LONG,
I PROMISE YOU.
- UNH!
- UH! WHAT'S COMING OUT
OF THE MONK'S MOUTH?
- DEMON WORMS.
- FROM INSIDE HIS BODY?
- YES. THE MONK
HAS BEEN POSSESSED
BY A DEMON WORM CHARMER.
- CAN'T HE BE SAVED?
- THERE MUST BE A CHARMER
CLOSE BY WHO'S MANIPULATING HIM.
WE NEED TO STEAL
HIS WORM BOTTLE AWAY
AND PLACE IT NEAR THE MONK,
AND THE DEMON WILL LEAVE
THE MONK'S BODY.
- UNH!
- OK, MYOGA,
LET'S HUNT DOWN THE CHARMER.
- WHY DO YOU NEED ME?
- KAGOME, WHAT'S GOING ON?
THERE SEEMS TO BE NO END
TO THE DEMONS.
- YEAH, AND INUYASHA'S
BEEN TIED UP.
- SANGO, I'M SO RELIEVED
YOU'RE HERE.
- MYOGA'S HERE?
- THINK YOU'LL BE SAFER
WITH HER THAN WITH ME?
- NOTHING PERSONAL.
- KAGOME, LOOK UP!
- HUH?
- THAT'S THE CHARMER.
I'M SURE OF IT.
- [GRUNTING]
MISSED HIM.
- I'LL GET HIM.
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
UNH.
DAMN IT. THESE SUTRA BEADS
ARE DRAINING MY STRENGTH.
I'M STARTING TO FEEL WEAK.
UNH!
HUH?
- SOON, YOU WON'T
HAVE ANY POWER LEFT
TO FIGHT WITH AT ALL,
SO YOU BETTER DECIDE
ON YOUR FATE.
DO YOU WANT TO BE
DEVOURED ALIVE,
OR DO YOU WANT ME
TO BE MORE BENEVOLENT
AND CHOP YOUR HEAD OFF FIRST?
I'M A DEMON WHO LOVES
TO EAT FLESH, DEAD OR KICKING,
SO MY APPETITE WILL BE
SATED EITHER WAY.
- DON'T GET YOUR HOPES UP
YET, YOU STINKING MONK.
YAH!
- UHH!
NOW DIE!
- YOU BETTER THINK ABOUT IT
BEFORE YOU KILL ME.
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN
REPAIR MIROKU'S WIND TUNNEL.
IF HIS HAND IS LEFT
AS IT IS,
ALL OF YOU, INCLUDING MIROKU,
WILL BE SUCKED INSIDE OF IT
BY THIS TIME TOMORROW.
- UNH!
AAH! UNH! AAH!
- EITHER WAY, YOU MUST
RESIGN YOURSELF TO THE FACT
THAT EVERYONE IN THIS TEMPLE
IS GOING TO DIE SOON.
- MASTER, THE POISON WORE OFF.
YOU CAN MOVE! OH!
NOT THE WIND TUNNEL!
- HACHI, PREPARE YOURSELF.
BOTH OF US WILL PROBABLY
GET SUCKED IN THIS TIME,
BUT IT'S BETTER THAN BEING
TORN LIMB FROM LIMB
AND EATEN BY A PACK OF DEMONS.
- [GASP]
I AGREE, MASTER.
I'M WITH YOU.
- READY?
WIND TUNNEL!
[ROARING]
HACHI, BRACE ME!
- YES, SIR!
- MIROKU?
- THE FOOL.
HE'LL SUCK IN EVERYTHING
AROUND HIM,
INCLUDING THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD.
- HIS SPELL IS WEAKENING.
AAH! UNH!
- UNH!
- GIVE IT A REST!
[GRUNTING]
I CAN'T HOLD MY GROUND!
AAH!
- AAH!
- UNH!
- AAH! UNH!
- INU...YASHA?
- DAMN IT!
IF YOU TRY TO USE
THAT WIND TUNNEL AGAIN,
I'LL TEAR YOUR STUPID ARM OFF!
[ROARING]
I DON'T CARE
IF YOU DIE OR NOT,
BUT YOU'RE NOT GONNA DO IT
WHILE I'M AROUND, YOU GOT THAT?
I WON'T BE ACCUSED
OF ABANDONING YOU.
I DON'T WANT NO GUILT TRIPS!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LAY
THAT RESPONSIBILITY ON ME!
YAH!
- OH, WOW.
- HE--HE BLEW UP THE DEMONS?
- [GASP]
THEY'VE BEEN DESTROYED?
- HUH?
WHAT...HAPPENED?
HUH?
- YOU FINALLY REALIZED
THE FULL POWER
OF THE TETSUSAIGA.
- OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
- WHOA!
[SIGH]
- OH!
- WHOA.
- I THINK HE'LL BE FINE NOW.
- HE'S TAKING SO LONG.
- HE HAS TO STITCH
THE WOUND VERY CAREFULLY.
WE DON'T WANT HIM TO RUSH.
- HMM, THE YOUNG FOOL.
HE SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL.
- MUSHIN, HOW'S MIROKU?
- HE'S SLEEPING.
YOU THERE. INUYASHA.
COME WITH ME.
WELL, DRUNKARD,
I HOPE YOU DID A GOOD JOB
STITCHING UP THE WIND TUNNEL.
- [SIGH]
I DID THE BEST THAT I COULD
TO REPAIR IT,
BUT THE WIND TUNNEL
HAS DEFINITELY SPREAD.
- DOES THAT MEAN THAT HIS LIFE
HAS BEEN SHORTENED?
HOW MUCH LONGER
DOES HE HAVE TO LIVE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MIROKU'S WIND TUNNEL
IS A GENERATIONAL CURSE
PLACED ON HIM AND HIS FAMILY
BY THE DEMON NARAKU.
IF NARAKU IS DESTROYED,
THEN THE CURSE WILL BE LIFTED,
AND MIROKU'S LIFE
WILL BE SPARED.
THE SOONER YOU GET HIM,
THE BETTER.
IT'S MIROKU'S ONLY HOPE.
- HMM.
- HE SURE PUTS ON
A STRONG FRONT, DOESN'T HE?
HOW DOES HE MANAGE
TO ALWAYS STAY SO LIGHTHEARTED?
- HMM. I BET THAT DEEP INSIDE,
HE WORRIES ABOUT
THE WIND TUNNEL CURSE
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
- UHH...
- HUH? YOU'RE AWAKE.
- HI, MIROKU.
- YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
THE MONK STITCHED UP
THE WIND TUNNEL.
- [GASP]
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOUR HAND?
- HMM?
- UNH!
- HUH!
- MASTER MIROKU.
- IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'VE
MADE A FULL RECOVERY.
- SOUNDS LIKE HE'S STILL
GOT A LOT OF LIFE LEFT IN HIM.
- HMM.
MIROKU'S BLOODLINE
IS TO BE FEARED.
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- SANGO HAD A YOUNGER BROTHER
NAMED KOHAKU.
HE DIED WHEN THEY FELL
INTO NARAKU'S TRAP.
IT'S SO SAD THAT THE SCAR
ON SANGO'S BACK
IS A CONSTANT REMINDER
OF HER LOSS.
INUYASHA IS ATTACKED
BY A DEMON SLAYER'S WEAPON,
AND SANGO'S EXPRESSION
HAS CHANGED.
COULD THAT BOY BE...
BUT HOW CAN THAT BE POSSIBLE?
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!