>> THE BIRDS ARE DWINDLING
IN NUMBERS!
>> MY LADY,
PLEASE TRY TO HOLD ON
JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
>> THANK GOODNESS.
>> MY LADY, WE ARE ACTUALLY
GOING TO BE SAVED, AREN'T WE?
>> MM-HMM.
KOHAKU, IT IS BECAUSE OF
YOUR HEROIC EFFORTS
THAT OUR LIVES WERE SPARED...
AND MY CHILD IS WITHOUT
A SINGLE SCRATCH.
>> YOU ARE JUST A BOY,
BUT YOU DID A FINE JOB, KOHAKU.
>> I AGREE.
YOU'LL BE REWARDED LATER.
HMM?
>> KOHAKU--
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> K--KOHAKU!
>> MY LADY, GET BACK FROM HIM!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
>> KOHAKU, TAKE THE INFANT.
KILL EVERYONE ELSE.
>> KOHAKU!
ANSWER ME!
>> WHY DO I HAVE TO KILL
THESE PEOPLE?
>> AAH!
UH--AH!
AAH!
>> DAMN YOU!
>> HAVE YOU GONE MAD?
>> UH!
>> AH!
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS.
WHAT'S THIS TERRIBLE FEELING?
>> TAKE THE INFANT
AND KILL ALL THE OTHERS.
>> UH!
AH!
>> NO.
I DON'T WANT TO.
>> UH--UH!
>> YOU ARE A TRAITOR.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO US?
[GASPS]
>> OH!
STOP.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
>> NO...
>> KOHAKU.
>> I DON'T WANT TO KILL THEM.
>> KOHAKU, CAN'T YOU TELL ME
WHO'S CONTROLLING YOUR HEART?
>> MY HEART?
>> KOHAKU!
>> HUH?
IT'S THAT LADY AGAIN.
>> THESE PEOPLE WEREN'T KILLED
BY THE BIRDS.
>> [PANTING]
HUH?
OH!
AH--UH!
>> KANNA...
SHE'S HERE?
WAIT A MINUTE--
THAT'S HAKUDOSHI'S OTHER HALF.
WHAT?
YOU WANT ME TO GO GET KOHAKU?
HUH?
KANNA'S ALREADY GONE.
>> HALF-DEMON, I'LL FINISH
YOU OFF FOR GOOD!
>> UH!
I'M GONNA KILL YOU HERE AND NOW,
AND PUT AN END TO YOUR SCOURGE.
UH!
YAH!
>> YOU'RE THROUGH!
>> UH!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS PRINCESS ABI'S BARRIER
JUST AS STRONG AS NARAKU'S?
>> IT MUST BE IF INUYASHA'S
TETSUSAIGA CAN'T EVEN
BREAK THROUGH IT.
>> BUT STILL, WE'VE GOTTA HELP!
>> HUH?
LITTLE WITCH!
>> KAGOME!
>> AH!
>> WHAT ABOUT ME?
UH--AAH!
SOMEBODY SAVE ME!
>> STAY BACK.
I DON'T NEED HELP,
I CAN HANDLE HER MYSELF.
[SCREECHING]
>> THE BIRDS ARE STARTING
TO GATHER AROUND.
>> HMM.
IT MUST MEAN THEY'VE SUCKED
ALL THE BLOOD FROM THE HUMANS
IN THAT CASTLE.
I EXPECTED MORE RESISTANCE
FROM A CASTLE THAT IS CONNECTED
WITH NARAKU, BUT IT SEEMS IT WAS
JUST AN ORDINARY HUMAN CASTLE.
>> ORDINARY HUMAN CASTLE?
BUT KOHAKU WAS INSIDE.
NO DOUBT UNDER NARAKU'S ORDERS.
>> I'M LEAVING FOR
THE TIME BEING.
YOUR LIFE HAS BEEN EXTENDED
FOR A WHILE.
>> HUH?
WHAT THE--
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> SHUT UP.
TAKING THE HUMAN BLOOD BACK
TO THE NEST IS MORE IMPORTANT
TO ME.
>> HAH.
I'M NOT LETTIN' YOU GET AWAY!
COME HERE!
>> STAY OUT OF MY WAY!
>> UH!
[SCREECHING]
>> HAH!
>> WIND SCAR!
>> WHA--DAMN IT ALL.
[SCREECHING]
>> SHE GOT AWAY AGAIN.
>> HUH--HEY, WHERE'S SANGO?
>> KOHAKU, YOU...
YOU DID IT AGAIN, DIDN'T YOU?
>> AGAIN?
WHAT DOES SHE MEAN?
>> KOHAKU...
>> AGAIN?
UH...
WHAT WAS THAT JUST NOW?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UH...
UH--UH--
>> KOHAKU!
>> WHO...IS SHE?
UH...
WHO AM I?
UH--UH...
>> [GASP]
KOHAKU!
>> MM.
>> AH!
KOHAKU...
[GROWLS]
>> NOW I REMEMBER.
I KILLED MY FATHER AND EVERYONE
ELSE WITH MY OWN 2 HANDS.
UH--
SISTER!
>> [GASP]
HEY!
>> I REMEMBER EVERYTHING NOW.
>> AH!
>> I KILLED MY FATHER AND
THE REST OF THE DEMON SLAYERS
WITH MY OWN 2 HANDS.
I EVEN TRIED TO KILL MY SISTER
SANGO.
I SHOULD'VE DIED THAT NIGHT,
BUT THEN HE CAME...
NARAKU.
KOHAKU, YOU'RE TREMBLING, I SEE.
YOU WANT TO FORGET IT ALL?
TO ERASE THE TERRIBLE THINGS
YOU'VE DONE HERE?
FORGET THEM,
FORGET EVERYTHING...
AND JOIN ME.
>> AH--AH!
UH!
>> [SCREAMS]
>> [YELLING]
>> DAMN YOU!
>> UH--AH!
>> AAH!
[YELLS]
UH!
>> JEEZ, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
YOU TRYING TO KILL YOURSELF?
>> [PANTING]
I DON'T CARE IF I DO DIE.
>> WHAT?
>> UH...
NARAKU.
I'LL KILL HIM, EVEN IF IT
COSTS BOTH OUR LIVES.
>> KOHAKU.
>> SANGO!
>> HMM?
>> ARE THEY ALL DEAD?
>> IT WOULD SEEM SO.
>> THE BIRDS DIDN'T DO THIS.
>> KOHAKU DID IT.
>> HUH?
>> HE KILLED THEM ALL.
>> SANGO, WHERE IS KOHAKU?
DID HE LEAVE AGAIN?
>> YES.
HE'S GONE.
BUT I COULDN'T GO AFTER HIM.
>> OH.
>> SANGO...
>> KOHAKU, YOU WERE COVERED
IN BLOOD.
EVEN IF I DID TAKE KOHAKU AWAY
FROM NARAKU, I WOULDN'T KNOW
HOW TO FREE HIS HEART
FROM NARAKU'S GRASP.
[SIGHS]
THERE IS ONE THING I COULD DO...
I COULD KILL KOHAKU MYSELF.
HUH?
[THUMPING]
>> THE BIRDS ARE GONE!
>> YOU MEAN OUR LIVES WERE
SPARED?
>> LOOK, NOT EVERYONE IN
THE CASTLE WAS KILLED.
>> KOHAKU!
>> HUH?
>> KOHAKU, WHERE ARE YOU, SON?
>> YOU KNOW KOHAKU?
>> HMM?
YES, HE WAS WORKING HERE
WITH US.
>> WE WERE SAVED BY THE BOY,
HE'S THE REASON WE'RE
STILL ALIVE.
>> AH--
>> IT WAS AMAZING.
HE ORDERED US TO STAY INSIDE
WHILE HE FOUGHT OFF
THE BIRD DEMONS.
>> HE LOOKED LIKE SUCH A MEEK
YOUNG LAD.
>> GOOD THING HE WASN'T,
OR WE'D BE DEAD.
>> KOHAKU...
>> YOUNG LADY, YOU KNOW KOHAKU,
I TAKE IT, WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE BOY, ANYWAY?
IS HE ALL RIGHT?
>> UH--
>> HUH?
>> KOHAKU IS A KIND BOY.
HE NORMALLY ISN'T THE KIND
OF PERSON WHO COULD DO SOM--
[SOBBING]
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> IT'S OK.
KOHAKU IS ALIVE.
[SOBS]
>> SANGO, CAN YOU PLEASE
DESCRIBE EXACTLY WHAT YOU SAW?
KOHAKU WAS THERE, SO THAT MUST
MEAN NARAKU IS CONNECTED IN
SOME WAY TO THE CASTLE.
>> MM-HMM.
I RUSHED AFTER KOHAKU,
AND FOLLOWED HIM TO THE CASTLE.
HE WAS ABOUT TO KILL A WOMAN
HOLDING AN INFANT.
>> AN INFANT?
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT INFANT LOOKED LIKE NARAKU'S
INCARNATION.
>> YOU SERIOUS?
>> HEY, WAIT, COME TO THINK
OF IT, IT LOOKED EXACTLY LIKE
NARAKU'S INFANT.
>> SO THAT'S IT.
THE INFANT IS THE CONNECTION
BETWEEN NARAKU AND THE CASTLE.
>> I STILL DON'T GET IT.
>> WHAT WERE YOU DOING
AT THAT CASTLE?
AND WHY WAS THAT INFANT
UH.
SO NARAKU WAS HIDING THAT INFANT
AT A HUMAN CASTLE.
WELL, ONE THING IS CERTAIN.
THAT INFANT MUST BE VERY
IMPORTANT TO NARAKU.
KOHAKU, ARE YOU SURE YOU WEREN'T
GIVEN AN CLUES ABOUT WHO THAT
CHILD IS?
>> NO.
>> HAH, I SEE.
>> HUH?
WHO IS THAT?
>> WHAT?
COME ON, DON'T YOU KNOW
ANYTHING?
THAT'S HAKUDOSHI, THE OTHER HALF
OF THE INFANT YOU WERE WITH.
HOLD IT!
WHY WAS THE INFANT SPLIT IN 2,
AND THEN 1 HALF HIDDEN IN
THE HUMAN CASTLE?
I REMEMBER!
THIS HALF DOESN'T HAVE A HEART.
THAT CHILD IS HAKUDOSHI'S HEART.
OR MAYBE EVEN...
NARAKU'S HEART.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAGURA?
IS THERE SOMETHING INTERESTING
ABOUT MY FACE?
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS,
GUYS, ARE YOU SURE WE'RE GOING
THE RIGHT WAY?
>> I'M SURE THIS IS
THE DIRECTION THAT PRINCESS ABI
WAS HEADED.
>> I DON'T EVEN PICK UP
THE SCENT OF THE BIRDS.
>> HMM.
JUDGING FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN,
THERE'S NO SIGN OF THEM IN
THIS VILLAGE.
>> LET'S KEEP GOING.
>> GOOD IDEA, WE STILL HAVE
LOTS OF DAYLIGHT LEFT,
SO WE MIGHT AS WELL KEEP ON
SEARCHING.
>> YEAH.
[SQUEAKS]
>> HMM?
SANGO.
>> HUH?
>> LET'S GO, SHALL WE?
>> UH--YEAH.
OH--RIGHT.
>> WHAT'LL WE DO NOW, INUYASHA?
IF PRINCESS ABI HAS TURNED ON
NARAKU, THERE'S NO GUARANTEE
THE NEST WILL LEAD TO HIM,
EVEN IF WE FIND IT.
>> OF COURSE IT WILL.
>> HERE.
>> THANKS.
>> NARAKU IS AFTER THE
HUMAN BLOOD THAT PRINCESS ABI'S
COLLECTING.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT THERE.
NARAKU INTENDS TO USE
HUMAN BLOOD TO CROSS INTO
THE OTHER WORLD TO WHERE
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD LIES.
WE STILL HAVEN'T QUITE FIGURED
OUT HOW NARAKU'S GOING TO
DO THAT, THOUGH.
[FIRE CRACKLES]
>> AHH.
SO, INUYASHA, ARE YOU JUST GONNA
LEAVE SANGO ALONE?
>> HUH?
>> SANGO'S BEEN DOWN
FOR SO LONG NOW.
SHE MUST BE WORRIED ABOUT
KOHAKU.
>> WHAT WILL I DO IF KOHAKU'S
COMMITTED EVEN MORE CRIMES
BY THE NEXT TIME I SEE HIM?
CAN I SAVE KOHAKU?
HUH?
MIROKU.
>> SO, SANGO.
MIND IF I SIT WITH YOU?
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOU SUFFERING ON YOUR OWN.
TELL ME, IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN
DO TO HELP COMFORT YOU?
>> JUST STAY HERE.
SIT BESIDE ME.
>> OF COURSE I WILL.
>> WOW, HE CASUALLY PUTS HIS ARM
AROUND HER SHOULDERS.
>> SHOULDERS?
HE'S NOT STROKING HER BUTT?
>> TAKE A LOOK.
>> YOU ARE SO IGNORANT,
INUYASHA.
MIROKU MIGHT BE A PERVERT BUT
EVEN HE KNOWS THERE'S A TIME
AND PLACE.
>> YEAH, SURE.
BUT THEY'RE ENGAGED TO MARRY,
RIGHT?
IT'S NOT LIKE SANGO WOULD
GET MAD ANYMORE.
>> YOU ARE SO TOTALLY DENSE
WHEN IT COMES TO WOMEN.
>> HEY, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH
YOU LOVE A PERSON, YOU'LL
DEFINITELY FALL OUT OF LOVE
IF THEY'RE INSENSITIVE
ALL THE TIME.
>> HAH.
IF MIROKU STOPS ACTING LIKE
A LECHER, WHAT'S LEFT OF HIM?
>> HIS WIND TUNNEL?
>> AND DON'T WORRY, SANGO,
I WON'T STROKE YOUR BOTTOM.
>> GOOD.
HANDS OFF FOR NOW.
>> HMM.
>> MOTHER, I ATTACKED THE CASTLE
BUT NARAKU WAS NOWHERE TO BE
FOUND.
NOT ALL WAS LOST, THOUGH.
I HAD THE BIRDS SUCK THE BLOOD
OUT OF THE HUMANS THERE.
>> FINE.
WITH ALL THE BLOOD YOU'VE
BROUGHT ME, THE POISON IN MY
BODY HAS BEEN GREATLY DILUTED.
YOU MUST STAY ON GUARD THOUGH,
ABI, I AM CERTAIN THAT
THE CASTLE YOU ATTACKED HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH NARAKU.
I'M SURE OF IT, BECAUSE
THE BARRIER AROUND THIS NEST
HAS VANISHED.
>> BARRIER?
>> YES.
WE NEVER ASKED HIM TO, BUT
NARAKU HAD HIDDEN OUR NEST BY
ERECTING A BARRIER AROUND IT.
>> DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE WORRIED
THAT THAT LOUSY HALF-DEMON IS
GOING TO TRY ATTACKING US HERE.
[SCREECHING]
>> SISTER.
>> KOHAKU.
>> [SNIFFS]
MM.
[SNIFFS]
THE SCENT OF THOSE BIRDS.
THAT MEANS WE MUST BE CLOSE
TO THE NEST.
HUH?
THEY'RE KIKYO'S SHIKIGAMI.
>> LADY KIKYO AWAITS.
>> SHE WAITS FOR YOU.
>> [MUSIC]
>> I MET WITH KIKYO,
BUT SHE HASN'T COMPLETELY
HEALED YET.
NO CHANCE.
YOU WAIT HERE.
>> THEN GIVE THIS TO KAGOME.
IT'S UP TO HER IF SHE CAN
USE IT OR NOT.
>> A SINGLE ARROW IS ENTRUSTED
TO ME, BUT WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
MEANWHILE, NARAKU BATTLES
PRINCESS ABI'S MOTHER, TEKKEI,
AND OPENS THE PATH THAT CONNECTS
THIS WORLD TO THE NEXT.
NEXT TIME, THE DEMON LINKED WITH
THE NETHERWORLD.
>> NARAKU TOOK DOWN THE BARRIER,
BUT IT'S A TRAP!