>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> INUYASHA LOSES HIS DEMONIC
POWERS ON THE SACRED GROUNDS OF
MOUNT HAKURAI AND IS HUNTED DOWN
BY JOKUTSU.
AND WHAT IS THE EERIE PRESENCE
THAT MIROKU AND SANGO HAVE COME
ACROSS?
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TO TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> INUYASHA!
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> [GRUNTING]
[THINKING] SEE?
I KNEW IT.
I'M NOT BEING PURIFIED.
[GRUNTING]
I'M GONNA MAKE IT!
>> ONE THING'S OBVIOUS,
INUYASHA.
YOU'RE IN A HURRY TO GET IN
THERE, AREN'T YOU?
PROBLEM IS, IF YOU GO ANY
FURTHER, EVEN A HALF DEMON LIKE
YOURSELF WILL BE PURIFIED.
>> [GRUNT]
>> GET GOING!
>> UGH!
[THINKING] SEE, I'M STILL...
HUH?
MY DEMONIC POWERS ARE GONE,
AND IT'S NOT EVEN THE NIGHT
OF THE NEW MOON!
DAMN IT!
IT'S THIS BARRIER'S FAULT!
HUH?
AGH!
>> IS THAT REALLY YOU AS A
MORTAL?
YOU'RE AS CUTE A HUMAN AS YOU
ARE A HALF DEMON.
>> JAKOTSU!
>> WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
[SLURP]
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THE TIME
WHEN I COULD FIGHT YOU AGAIN,
INUYASHA.
>> ARGH!
>> HA.
>> HA HA HA!
>> [PANTING]
MIROKU!
>> RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
[PANTING]
>> WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT IT'D LEAD
TO A PLACE LIKE THIS?
>> AND IT LOOKS LIKE A MOUNTAIN
TEMPLE.
[THINKING] THE LEVEL OF PURITY
HERE MUST MEAN WE'RE AT THE
CENTER OF THE SACRED GROUNDS.
>> [PANTING]
>> A LIVING BUDDHA!
>> IS IT SAINT HOKUSHIN?
>> [GASPING]
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> SAINT HOKUSHIN IS STILL
ALIVE?
>> WHO ARE YOU?
WHY DO YOU VIOLATE MY SACRED
TERRITORY?
>> HOW CAN A MUMMY BE ALIVE?
>> YOU'RE THE MONK WHO WENT BY
THE NAME SAINT HOKUSHIN, AREN'T
YOU?
>> CORRECT.
MY NAME IS HOKUSHIN.
>> HAS NARAKU SOMEHOW BROUGHT
HIM BACK TO LIFE?
>> TELL ME THIS, SAINT HOKUSHIN.
WORD HAS IT THAT DURING YOUR
LIFETIME, YOU WERE A MAN OF HIGH
MORALS AND YOU WORKED HARD TO
SAVE MANY PEOPLE.
HOW IS IT THAT YOU NOW ASSIST
NARAKU?
YOUR POWERS ARE UNDENIABLE.
YOU HAVE THE ABILITY TO LAY DOWN
THIS STRONG AND PURE BARRIER.
IT'S UNTHINKABLE THAT YOU'RE
ASSISTING NARAKU BECAUSE YOU'RE
UNABLE TO SEE THROUGH TO HIS
EVIL NATURE.
>> I KNOW WHAT HE IS.
BUT WHETHER HE'S A DEMON OF
GREAT WICKEDNESS OR NOT IS NOT
MY CONCERN.
I AM MERELY CARRYING OUT MY OWN
DESIRES.
>> HMM?
>> [GROANING]
>> HUH?
SHIPPO!
>> [GROAN]
KIRARA, IS THE BARRIER HARD ON
YOU, TOO?
>> [SQUEAK]
>> OH!
>> [THINKING] I HOPE YOU'RE ALL
RIGHT.
HURRY AND COME BACK IF IT GETS
TOO DIFFICULT FOR YOU.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING TO INUYASHA?
HE'S TAKING SO LONG IN THERE.
>> EVEN A HALF DEMON LIKE HIM
WOULD FIND IT HARD ON SACRED
GROUNDS.
MAYBE HE'S ALREADY BITTEN THE
DUST.
>> HUH?
>> YOU THINK HE'S DEAD?
>> LISTEN, YOU TWO.
[KNUCKLES CRACKING]
>> [GROANING]
>> HEY, WHAT'S THAT FOR?
>> WE'RE JUST WORRIED ABOUT HIM,
THAT'S ALL.
>> JUST KEEP YOUR MOUTHS SHUT.
>> KAGOME?
>> HMM?
>> I'M SURE INUYASHA'S ALL
RIGHT.
>> HMM, THANKS, SHIPPO, FOR
SAYING THAT.
>> HUH?
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
DAMN IT!
>> HA HA HA!
THAT'S THE WAY.
KEEP RUNNING.
I WANT TO HAVE MY FILL OF FUN.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW OFTEN I'VE
DREAMT OF CUTTING YOU UP.
>> [SIGH]
>> YOU WERE ADORABLE WHEN YOU
HAD THOSE DOG EARS, BUT YOUR
HUMAN FORM IS SO LUSCIOUS IT
MAKES ME WANT TO TAKE YOU IN MY
ARMS.
>> YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
EVERYTHING YOU SAY MAKES ME
WANNA PUKE.
>> HA HA HA!
>> [GROANING]
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
EVEN THIS ROBE OF THE FIRE RAT
MUST'VE LOST ITS POWER IN HERE.
IT'S NOT SERVING AS ARMOR
ANYMORE.
>> [SLURP]
HA HA HA.
I'LL SLICE YOU UP PIECE BY
LITTLE PIECE.
ONCE I GET GOING, EVEN SMART
MOUTHS LIKE YOU QUICKLY BECOME
SUBMISSIVE.
AND IN THE END, YOU'LL BE ON
YOUR KNEES CRYING AND BEGGING
ME.
YOU'LL CRY, "JOKUTSU, JUST HOLD
ME IN YOUR ARMS FOR A WHILE,
PLEASE!"
>> HA!
I'D STOP WITH THE RIDICULOUS
STORIES IF I WERE YOU.
OR I'LL CRACK YOUR HEAD OPEN!
>> OH, YEAH, THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU CRY!
>> [GROANING]
[THINKING] I GOTTA BLOCK HIS
ATTACKS RIGHT OR I WON'T BE ABLE
TO COUNTER HIS MOVES.
THEN I'LL BE IN DEEP TROUBLE.
>> RUN, MY PRETTY.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE EXCITING
THAN THE SIGHT OF FLEEING PREY!
>> [GRUNTING]
[THINKING] DAMN, THIS IS BAD.
>> HA HMM.
>> THE BARRIER YOU CREATED BY
YOUR OWN POWERS IS HIDING AND
PROTECTING THE EVIL NARAKU.
YOU KNOW THAT, AND YET YOU DON'T
STOP!
>> LONG AGO, WHEN I WAS ALIVE,
I NEVER HESITATED TO DO WHATEVER
I COULD TO HELP A PEOPLE.
[BELL RINGING]
>> [CRYING]
HMM?
>> I ENTERED NIRVANA AFTER
SEVERAL YEARS OF THE GREAT
FAMINE.
DISEASE WAS RAMPANT, AND CORPSES
LAY STREWN EVERYWHERE ON THE
GROUND.
THUS WAS THE ERA WE LIVED IN.
>> FORGIVE ME, YOUR HOLINESS,
BUT THAT MAN IS EVIL.
HE ATTACKED OUR VILLAGE.
>> YOU NEEDN'T SAVE A WICKED MAN
LIKE HIM!
>> YOU ARE MISTAKEN.
ALL MEN BOTH GOOD AND EVIL ARE
WORTHY OF SALVATION.
>> SAINT HOKUSHIN.
THANK--THANK YOU.
[GRUNT]
>> MAY YOU REST IN PEACE.
>> SAINT HOKUSHIN, PLEASE HELP
US.
>> THERE'S NOTHING TO EAT IN THE
VILLAGE.
WE HAVE NO FOOD AT ALL.
>> SAINT HOKUSHIN, HELP US,
PLEASE.
>> WE BEG OF YOU.
>> [GRUNT]
>> [PEOPLE GASP AND SHOUT]
>> THE DAY CAME WHEN I
PERSONALLY BECAME ILL AND
COLLAPSED WHILE TENDING THE
SICK.
THE PEOPLE GATHERED AROUND,
LAMENTING MY POOR HEALTH.
>> IF YOU'RE GONE, WHAT WILL WE
DO, SAINT HOKUSHIN?
HOW WILL WE SURVIVE?
>> WHO WILL SAVE US IF NOT YOU?
>> I HAD TO GIVE THEM AN ANSWER.
YOU SHOULD NOT FEAR, MY GOOD
PEOPLE, FOR I WILL BECOME A
LIVING BUDDHA AND WILL LOOK
AFTER THE PEOPLE OF THIS LAND
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
>> AHH.
>> I FULFILLED MY PROMISE, AND I
WAS BURIED ALIVE IN FRONT OF ALL
THE VILLAGERS.
>> THAT'S HOW YOU WERE ABLE TO
BECOME A LIVING BUDDHA.
>> MY ONLY CONNECTION TO THE
OUTIDE WORLD WAS A SHORT PIECE
OF BAMBOO FOR BREATHING.
[BELL RINGING]
>> IN THE PIT, I CONTINUOUSLY
RANG A SMALL BELL.
WHEN THE BELL FELL SILENT,
IT WOULD TELL THOSE OUTSIDE
THAT I WAS DEAD.
OUTSIDE, EVERYONE PRAYED FOR MY
UNHINDERED AND MAGNIFICENT ENTRY
INTO NIRVANA.
>> HMM?
[MUNCHING]
>> THEY WERE WISHING FOR MY
DEATH.
[GROANING]
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE,
I WAS OVERCOME WITH REGRET.
I HAD AN ATTACHMENT TO LIFE, AND
A FEAR OF THE GREAT DARKNESS.
NO!
I'VE DONE EVERYTHING IN MY POWER
TO HELP PEOPLE!
SO WHY DO I HAVE TO DIE?
[SOBBING]
AND SO I DIED.
MY REMAINS WERE SANCTIFIED AS A
LIVING BUDDHA, BUT MY SOUL WAS
LEFT BEHIND IN THE DARKNESS FOR
A VERY LONG TIME WITH NO HOPE OF
SALVATION.
AND THEN CAME HIS VOICE.
>> HATE THEM.
HATE THEM.
NO ONE CAN BLAME YOU.
>> HUH?
>> HOW TRAGIC.
EVEN THOUGH THEY REVERED YOU AS
A HOLY SAINT, THEY NEVER ALLOWED
YOU TO HAVE DOUBTS OR TO SUFFER.
NO, NOT ONE OF THEM SPARED YOU A
SINGLE THOUGHT AS A MAN.
>> HE SPOKE OF THINGS I'D NEVER
DARED TO ADMIT.
EVEN TO MYSELF.
>> DON'T DECEIVE YOURSELF ANY
LONGER.
YOU WANT TO LIVE, NOT SACRIFICE
YOUR LIFE.
COME, JOIN ME.
LIVE WITH ME AND I SHALL TAKE
CARE OF YOU.
>> DO YOU BLAME ME?
CAN YOU HATE ME FOR MY CHOICE?
>> I AM NO SAINT MYSELF.
I HAVE NO INTENTION OF JUDGING
YOU.
ON THE OTHER HAND, I CANNOT
ALLOW A BARRIER TO STAND AND
PROTECT THE LIKES OF NARAKU!
[GRUNT]
>> MY BARRIER IS INPENETRABLE.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> MIROKU!
>> I'M ALL RIGHT.
>> CURSE THAT MUTT CAUSING
KAGOME ALL THIS WORRY.
WHAT'S TAKING HIM SO LONG?
>> HUH?
UH, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> THAT MUTT'S TAKEN WAY TOO
LONG.
I'M GOING TO GO AFTER HIM TO SEE
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
>> KOUGA, ARE YOU CRAZY?
>> I KNOW IT'S CRAZY.
>> DON'T DO IT.
>> HUH? WHAT?
>> LET'S JUST TRUST INUYASHA
AND WAIT HERE FOR HIM.
>> [PANTING]
>> TOO BAD YOUR BODY'S NOT
COOPERATING.
HA!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> THIS ISN'T VERY MUCH FUN.
HOW ABOUT SOME MORE SCREAMING
AND CRYING FROM YOU?
>> [GRUNTING AND PANTING]
>> HA HA HA.
WELL, AT LEAST I'VE GOT YOU
PANTING GOOD AND HARD.
>> [THINKING] WRETCHED INUYASHA.
I'D HOPED HE'D AT LEAST ME ABLE
TO WOUND JAKOTSU.
>> [SIGH]
DAMN HIM!
>> [THINKING]
HE CAN HARDLY MOVE.
JAKOTSU'S GOING TO TORTURE HIM
TO DEATH.
>> COME.
IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR OUR
EMBRACE.
OUR EMBRACE MADE SLICK WITH YOUR
BLOOD.
>> [GRUNTING AND PANTING]
DAMN!
MY VISIONS'S GOING ON ME.
>> IT'S TIME TO GIVE IT UP,
INUYASHA.
DON'T WORRY.
I WON'T KILL YOU RIGHT AWAY.
I WANT TO SPEND SOME TIME WITH
YOU FIRST.
>> NOW!
>> [THINKING] THAT WAS CLOSE.
THAT LITTLE PUNK WAS AIMING FOR
MY JEWEL SHARD.
>> I DON'T HAVE TIME TO SPEND
PLAYING WITH YOU ALL DAY.
HUH?
>> HA!
YOU'RE THREATENING ME WITH THAT
DULL OLD SWORD?
>> [GRUNT]
>> YOU DON'T SCARE ME.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HMM.
INUYASHA.
DON'T PASS OUT.
I WANT TO HEAR LOTS OF SCREAMING
FROM YOU.
>> [THINKING] I'M IN TROUBLE
NOW.
I'VE LOST TOO MUCH BLOOD.
I WAS HOPING I CAN CATCH HIM OFF
GUARD.
>> COME ON, CRY FOR ME.
WHERE'S THE FUN IF YOU DON'T
START WHIMPERING?
>> TAKE THIS!
>> IT'S USELESS.
>> PLACE SOME OF YOUR SUTRAS ON
MY HIRAIKOTSU.
>> RIGHT.
HAH!
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE GOES!
>> HUH?
>> [GRUNT]
IT'S NOT WORKING.
>> IT'S USELESS.
THE POWERS OF A NOVICE MONK LIKE
YOURSELF CANNOT POSSIBLY BREAK
MY POWERFUL BARRIER.
>> SO IT SEEMS.
FORGIVE ME, BUT YOU MUST BE
VANQUISHED.
>> [GASP]
>> RESISTING MY WIND TUNNEL?
>> [GROANING]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GRUNT]
>> IF YOU THINK YOU CAN KILL ME,
THEN HURRY UP AND GET ON WITH
IT.
>> HA HA HA.
WHAT'S THE RUSH?
WE'VE GOT TIME.
>> [THINKING] IT'S THEM.
[ALOUD] MIROKU.
SANGO.
>> HMM.
[THINKING] MOUNT HAKURAI.
WHAT ON EARTH IS GOING ON THERE?
>> THE BARRIER'S BROKEN!
>> [GROANING]
>> [GRUNT]
>> SANYOSHO!
>> [THINKING] MOUNT HAKURAI.
THE POWER OF THE SACRED GROUND
IS WEAKENING.
[ALOUD] SOMETHING IS ESCAPING
THE MOUNTAIN.
>> [GROAN]
>> I'LL FINISH YOU OFF IF THAT'S
WHAT YOU WANT.
AT LEAST GIVE ME ONE SWEET
LITTLE SCREAM OF AGONY.
>> GRR...
>> HUH?
>> [THINKING] NOW WHAT?
THE DEMONS ARE STIRRED UP ALL OF
A SUDDEN.
>> HMM?
WHAT WAS THAT?
THE DEMONS!
THEY'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE ABLE
TO PASS THROUGH THE BARRIER.
HUH?
[GRUNT]
COME AND GET IT.
>> [GRUNT]
DAMN, THERE'S TOO MANY OF THEM.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> OH!
MMM.
IT FEELS LIKE THE BARRIER IS
DISSIPATING.
HUH?
[GRUNTING]
MIROKU.
SANGO.
I TAKE IT YOU'RE SAFE.
YOU MUST'VE SUCCEEDED IN TAKING
DOWN THE BARRIER.
HEH HEH HEH.
I CAME TO RESCUE YOU, AND YOU
ENDED UP RESCUING ME.
>> SO, YOU GOT YOUR DEMONIC
POWERS BACK.
>> YOU'RE STUPIDER THAN I
THOUGHT, JAKOTSU.
YOU DIDN'T KILL ME WHEN YOU
COULD, AND NOW IT'S GONNA COST
YOU YOUR LIFE.
>> I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
I ONLY GET EXCITED WHEN I CAN
CUT MY VICTIMS UP NICE AND SLOW.
BESIDES, I'VE DIED ONCE ALREADY.
I WAS UNEXPECTEDLY BROUGHT BACK
TO LIFE AND ABLE TO MEET A SWEET
THING LIKE YOU.
TALK ABOUT A BONUS.
>> SPARE ME THE DETAILS.
I CAN TELL WE'RE NEVER GOING TO
HAVE A NORMAL CONVERSATION.
>> WELL, THINGS ARE HEATING UP
AROUND HERE.
SO, I GUESS THE FUN'S OVER.
I'LL TAKE THOSE DOG EARS OF
YOURS AS A SOUVENIR, THOUGH.
>> YEAH, RIGHT!
[GRUNTING]
>> HEH HEH HEH.
ONCE I BLOW ON THIS SWORD,
YOU'LL BE SLASHED INTO PIECES.
>> GRR...
>> BYE-BYE, INUYASHA.
OF ALL THE MEN WHO HAVE DIED BY
MY SWORD, I HAVE TO SAY, I LIKE
YOU THE BEST.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> KIKYO COMES INTO CONTACT WITH
SAINT HOKUSHIN.
MEANWHILE, INUYASHA'S POWERS
RETURN, AND HIS BATTLE WITH
JAKOTSU COMES TO ITS CLIMAX.
>> FORGIVE ME, JAKOTSU, BUT I
NEED EVERY SACRED JEWEL SHARD I
CAN GET MY HANDS ON.
>> WHAT THE HECK.
I'VE HAD MY SHARE OF FUN.
>> BANKOTSU'S ANGER FLARES AFTER
LOSING ALL HIS COMRADES.
NEXT TIME, "FARE THEE WELL:
JAKOTSU'S REQUIEM."
>> BAND OF 7.
LET THIS BE OUR FINAL BATTLE.