>> HUH?
AHH!
HELP!
UHH.
HUH?
AAH!
>> COME BACK.
THE OLD MAN RAN AWAY.
>> A VILLAGE OF DEMON WOMEN?
>> IT'S TRUE, I SAW THEM
WITH MY OWN EYES LAST NIGHT.
I WENT INTO THE FOREST TO GATHER
HERBS AND LOST MY WAY.
I WANDERED AROUND FOR A TIME
AND FINALLY ENDED UP NEAR
A MARSH.
SOME WOMEN WERE ON A CLIFF
ABOVE, HOLDING SOMETHING.
THEY THREW IT INTO THE MARSH.
>> WHAT WAS IT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA?
>> I'M CERTAIN IT WAS
A HUMAN BODY,
A BODY THAT HAD BEEN SKINNED.
HUMANS WOULD NEVER DO SUCH
A TERRIBLE THING.
IT HAD TO BE THE WORK
OF DEMON WOMEN.
>> DEMON WOMEN?
THAT'S CREEPY.
>> IT'S RATHER STRANGE THAT
I DON'T FEEL ANY DEMONIC AURA
COMING FROM AROUND HERE.
>> KAGOME, DO YOU SENSE ANY
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS?
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> IF THERE AREN'T ANY
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T BOTHER
GOING TO SUCH A DANGEROUS PLACE.
>> THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE WRONG.
>> HUH?
>> WE HAVE TO CHECK EVERY AREA
THAT'S EVEN THE SLIGHTEST BIT
SUSPICIOUS.
>> SANGO IS RIGHT.
THAT IS THE ONLY WAY TO MAKE
SURE THAT WE CAN GET THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS BEFORE NARAKU DOES.
>> RIGHT.
NARAKU IS NOTHING BUT EVIL.
WE CAN'T LET HIM FINISH CREATING
AN IMPURE SHIKON JEWEL.
>> UHH.
>> HUH?
>> WOMAN, YOU MUST TELL ME,
IS THERE A VILLAGE NEARBY?
UHH, OHH...
>> OH, YOU POOR MAN,
YOU'RE INJURED.
>> I SEE.
YOU SUFFERED A DEFEAT
IN THE WAR.
>> YES.
I COULDN'T HELP NOTICE,
THIS IS A STRANGE VILLAGE,
INDEED.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY STRANGE?
>> I HAD A FAIRLY GOOD
LOOK AROUND.
THERE ARE ONLY WOMEN HERE.
>> THAT'S CORRECT, THERE ARE
NO MEN LIVING IN THIS VILLAGE.
THEY ALL DIED IN BATTLE.
>> OH, I SEE.
THAT'S A SHAME.
>> PLEASE HAVE SOME FOOD
AND DRINK.
I'M SURE YOU MUST BE FAMISHED.
>> HMM.
THEN WHERE ARE THE CHILDREN
AND THE ELDERLY?
AH?
UHH.
OHH.
>> WAKANA, TAKE THIS MAN
INTO THE SHRINE AND AWAIT
MY INSTRUCTIONS.
>> YES, RIGHT.
>> UHH?
WAKANA.
AH, WAKANA!
UHH!
>> AAH!
>> MMM.
UHH?
I MUST HAVE FALLEN ASLEEP.
WHERE AM I?
THIS LOOKS LIKE A SHRINE.
A PAINTING.
WHY IS IT GLOWING LIKE THIS?
>> [LAUGHTER]
>> [GASP]
>> UHH.
OHH, AAH!
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
MIROKU?
>> I THINK I SENSE
A DEMONIC AURA JUST NOW.
>> YOU POSITIVE?
>> YES, IT WAS ONLY FOR
AN INSTANT,
BUT I DEFINITELY FELT IT.
>> UHH.
>> REMEMBER THAT OLD MAN
MENTIONED A MARSH WITH
DEMON WOMEN?
>> YES, THIS IS PROBABLY
THE PLACE.
>> LOOK OVER THERE, SOMETHING
IS FLOATING DOWNSTREAM!
>> YES, IT'S A MAN.
>> UHH...
>> IS HE DEAD?
>> UH-UH, HE'S ALIVE.
>> CAN'T YOU BE A BIT MORE
GENTLE WITH THE POOR MAN?
>> I GO BY THE NAME SHINOSUKE.
>> HERE, DRINK THIS UP.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HE'S GOTTA BE THE GLOOMIEST
GUY I'VE EVER MET.
>> COULD YOU NOT BE RUDE
FOR A CHANGE?
>> SHINOSUKE, YOU MENTIONED
EARLIER THAT YOU WERE LOOKING
FOR YOUR MISSING FIANCEE.
WHAT EXACTLY DID YOU MEAN
BY THAT?
>> WELL, JUST 3 DAYS
BEFORE OUR WEDDING CEREMONY,
I WAS CALLED INTO BATTLE.
I WAS SERIOUSLY INJURED.
A FULL 2 YEARS PASSED BEFORE
I WAS ABLE TO RETURN HOME.
NOT LONG AGO, I FINALLY RETURNED
TO MY HOMETOWN.
BUT THE VILLAGE HAD BEEN
BURNED TO THE GROUND.
AND MY FIANCE, WAKANA,
WAS NOWHERE TO BE FOUND.
I SEARCHED FOR HER, NOT KNOWING
IF SHE WAS DEAD OR ALIVE.
THAT'S WHEN I HEARD OF A VILLAGE
INHABITED SOLELY BY WOMEN.
>> OH, A VILLAGE OF ONLY WOMEN?
>> I HEARD THAT THE VILLAGE WAS
MADE UP OF WOMEN WHO'D LOST
THEIR HUSBANDS AND CHILDREN
TO WAR.
AND THAT THEY LIVED TOGETHER
IN ORDER TO SUPPORT EACH OTHER
DURING THEIR TIME OF NEED.
>> HMM?
>> WHEN I HEARD, I THOUGHT THAT
PERHAPS WAKANA HAD GIVEN UP ON
MY RETURN AND HAD JOINED THEM.
>> DO YOU THINK THIS HAS
ANYTHING TO DO WITH THAT VILLAGE
OF DEMON WOMEN THE OLD MAN
TOLD US ABOUT?
>> YES, IT HAS TO BE MORE
THAN A COINCIDENCE.
>> I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
WE WILL ACCOMPANY YOU
TO THIS VILLAGE.
>> THANKS FOR OFFERING,
BUT HOW WOULD WE FIND IT?
>> WE DON'T HAVE TO.
THEY'VE COME LOOKING FOR US,
SO THAT SOLVES PART OF
THE PROBLEM.
>> YES, THIS IS INDEED A VILLAGE
FOR WOMEN WHO HAVE LOST
THEIR LOVED ONES.
TOGETHER, WE MANAGE TO EEK OUT
A LIVING HERE.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS WAKANA
YOU ARE SEARCHING FOR
IS NOT WITH US.
LOOK FOR YOURSELF.
>> YES, I SEE.
>> SHE'S NOT HERE.
>> HOW SAD FOR HIM.
>> WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
>> I'LL KEEP SEARCHING FOR HER,
I CAN'T LET MYSELF GIVE UP.
I LOVE WAKANA, SHE'S THE ONLY
WOMAN FOR ME.
>> HE'S SO DEVOTED TO HER.
>> SHE'S A LUCKY PERSON.
>> [GASP]
>> UHH, DON'T READ ANYTHING
INTO THAT.
>> HMM.
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY, MIROKU?
>> HMM?
>> DO YOU FEEL ANY EVIL
OR DEMONIC AURAS?
[SNIFFING]
I ONLY PICK UP THE SCENT
OF THE WATER.
NOTHING SUSPICIOUS, EXCEPT...
>> YOU MUST BE SO LONELY,
SURROUNDED ONLY BY WOMEN.
>> WERE YOU EVEN LISTENING?
>> YES, IT IS LONELY.
>> UHH!
OH, WELL, I GUESS THERE'S
NO DEMONIC AURA AROUND.
HUH?
>> OH, THE SCENT OF DEATH.
>> MIROKU, ISN'T IT TIME
WE LEFT?
IT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE THIS
IS THE VILLAGE OF DEMON WOMEN
WE ARE LOOKING FOR, DOES IT?
>> WHAT, LEAVE NOW?
>> MAY I HAVE A WORD WITH YOU,
TRAVELERS?
THE PATHS AT NIGHT ARE
DANGEROUS.
WE HAVE LITTLE TO OFFER YOU,
BUT PLEASE...
>> STAY THE NIGHT HERE, AND
START OUT FRESH IN THE MORNING.
>> THANK YOU,
WE WOULD BE MUCH OBLIGED.
>> PARDON ME, MONK?
>> GOOD, THE LADIES CAN FOLLOW
ME TO THEIR QUARTERS.
GENTLEMEN, THAT WAY PLEASE.
>> HUH?
>> SEPARATE ROOMS?
>> INUYASHA, PERHAPS WE SHOULD
CONTINUE OUR JOURNEY TONIGHT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU WERE THE ONE WHO WAS
SO EAGER TO STAY HERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> I'VE RECONSIDERED.
>> WHAT, YOU DON'T LIKE ROOMING
WITH US MEN FOLK?
>> HUH? GRR...
HUH.
>> YOU SEE, WE'RE A LONELY
LITTLE VILLAGE OF WOMEN,
SO WE'RE HAPPY TO HAVE
A GUEST ONCE IN A WHILE.
>> ISN'T IT GREAT NOT HAVING
TO CAMP OUTSIDE?
>> SURE, I APPRECIATE THE ROOM,
BUT SHOULDN'T WE REALLY
BE LOOKING FOR THE VILLAGE
OF DEMON WOMEN?
OH, MIROKU,
HE'S SUCH A WOMANIZER.
>> UHH.
>> WHERE ARE YOU, WAKANA?
>> SHINOSUKE, YOU'RE ALIVE
AFTER ALL.
I'M SO GLAD.
ALL THIS TIME,
I THOUGHT YOU DIED IN BATTLE.
>> DO YOU WISH TO RETURN
TO YOUR LOVED ONE'S SIDE?
I SHALL LET YOU SEE HIM
AGAIN SOON, BUT IT WILL BE HERE.
BRING THE MAN HERE,
BRING HIM TO ME.
>> YES.
>> TELL ME SOMETHING, MIROKU.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT SANGO?
>> HUH?
UHH, HMM.
>> AT MOUNT HAKUREI,
YOU AND SANGO WERE ALONE
TOGETHER FOR QUITE A WHILE.
>> YEAH, SO WHAT ABOUT IT?
>> DID ANYTHING HAPPEN BETWEEN
YOU THERE?
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
>> I AM THE WIND, REMEMBER?
>> UHH!
AAH!
SANGO!
UH.
SAY SOMETHING TO ME, SANGO!
>> HOW VERY TOUCHING, MONK.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU MIGHT HAVE
LIVED A LITTLE LONGER IF YOU'D
ONLY GONE ON AHEAD WITHOUT HER.
[GROWLING]
>> UHH!
>> YOU CAN'T USE YOUR
WIND TUNNEL, THOUGH,
FOR FEAR OF THE INSECT'S POISON.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHO YOU'RE
DEALING WITH.
WHAT MEANING DOES MY LIFE
HAVE WITHOUT THE WOMAN
I DEEPLY CARE FOR?
I WOULD SACRIFICE MY LIFE
FOR HERS.
AAH, WIND TUNNEL!
THE INSECT POISON IS SPREADING
THROUGH MY BODY.
HMM.
HUH?
>> SO WHICH IS IT,
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN OR NOT?
>> NOTHING HAPPENED BETWEEN
SANGO AND I, YOU HAVE MY WORD.
WELL, WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
>> HEY, SANGO, ARE YOU SURE
THERE'S NOTHING BETWEEN
YOU AND MIROKU?
>> HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, NOTHING?
I DON'T FOLLOW.
>> WHEN WE WERE AT
MOUNT HAKUREI, YOU TWO WERE
ALL ALONE FOR QUITE A WHILE,
RIGHT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY GOOD MEMORIES
OF THE TIME YOU SPENT TOGETHER?
[GROWLING]
>> UHH.
SANGO, DON'T STAY HERE,
GO ON WITHOUT ME.
>> NO, NOT UNLESS
YOU'RE WITH ME.
>> I THINK I MIGHT HAVE
PUSHED MYSELF TOO FAR THIS TIME.
YOU AT LEAST HAVE TO MAKE IT
OUT OF THIS ALIVE, FOR ME, OK?
>> NO!
IF YOU CAN'T GO ON,
THEN WE'LL DIE HERE TOGETHER.
>> SANGO...
>> I'M ALMOST POSITIVE I SAID
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
OH, MIROKU'S WOMANIZING HASN'T
CHANGED ONE BIT SINCE THEN,
THOUGH.
>> COME ON, ARE YOU SURE
NOTHING ACTUALLY HAPPENED?
>> HEY, CUT IT OUT, KAGOME!
MIROKU AND I DON'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF RELATIONSHIP.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOUR FEELINGS?
YOU LIKE MIROKU, DON'T YOU?
>> HMM?
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS, KAGOME,
ME LIKE THAT PERVERT?
>> OOPS, SORRY!
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING ANYONE,
SANGO.
>> HE'S IRRESPONSIBLE,
A DELINQUENT, AND LIES WITHOUT
ANY REMORSE.
HUH.
>> TOO BAD.
'CAUSE I'VE BEEN WATCHING
MIROKU, AND I REALLY GET
THE FEELING THAT HE LIKES YOU,
SANGO.
>> WHY? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I JUST GET THAT FEELING,
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE HIS
SPECIAL GIRL.
HE REALLY SEEMS TO CARE
ABOUT YOU A LOT.
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> YOU THINK SO, TOO,
DON'T YOU, KIRARA?
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, KIRARA?
>> OH, I SEE.
YOU LOST YOUR HUSBAND IN BATTLE,
HOW SAD.
>> YES.
>> IF THERE'S ANY WAY THAT
I COULD LEND YOU SOME COMFORT,
PLEASE, LET ME KNOW.
>> I APPRECIATE YOUR OFFER,
THANK YOU.
>> HUH?
SANGO--
>> I'M GOING TO SLEEP.
>> COME ON, INUYASHA,
ARE YOU JUST GOING TO LET
MIROKU DO THAT?
>> WHATEVER.
IT'S WAY BETTER THAN HAVING
HIM HERE SIGHING ALL NIGHT
ABOUT THE WOMEN.
>> OH, SANGO'S GONNA BE FURIOUS!
>> WHY'S THAT?
>> UH, COME ON, ARE YOU REALLY
THAT STUPID?
>> AAH!
>> LET ME GO!
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> HMM?
>> I'M GOING TO SLEEP, I'LL
BE LEAVING HERE AT FIRST LIGHT.
I MUST CONTINUE MY SEARCH
FOR WAKANA, AND I NEED TO MAKE
USE OF EVERY HOUR OF DAYLIGHT.
>> SURE, DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
>> I FEEL SO SORRY FOR SANGO.
SHE SHOULD SWALLOW HER PRIDE
AND STOP MIROKU.
I GUESS THAT'S TOO MUCH TO ASK.
HUH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, KIRARA?
SANGO!
>> QUIET!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> I'M GOING TO FOLLOW THEM.
>> HEY, WAIT!
I'LL GET INUYASHA AND MIROKU
TO COME ALONG, TOO.
THEY'RE PROBABLY CLOSE BY,
SO IT'LL JUST TAKE A SEC--
>> NEVER MIND, THERE'S NO TIME
TO LOOK FOR THEM.
>> WAIT, SANGO.
>> HUH?
HMM...
WHAT'S THIS SCENT?
WATER?
NO...IT'S THE SMELL OF
SOMETHING ALIVE.
A WHOLE BUNCH OF SOMETHINGS.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
>> YOU TWO GO BACK TO SLEEP.
>> INUYASHA!
SANGO WENT OFF TO FOLLOW
THE WOMEN ON HER OWN.
>> SHE WHAT?
>> THE SMELL OF LIVING
WATER CREATURES?
>> YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT I JUST PICKED UP THE SCENT
ALL OF A SUDDEN, TOO.
JUST AS THE WOMEN STARTED
TO MOVE.
>> HUH...
>> SHINOSUKE.
>> WAKANA, WAKANA.
HOW I'VE SEARCHED FOR YOU,
MY DEAREST.
>> PLEASE, THIS WAY, MONK,
KEEP COMING.
>> INTERESTING.
INSIDE A SHRINE?
WE'LL BRING ON THE WRATH
OF THE DEITY KANNON FOR THIS.
HUH?
HMM...
>> THEY'RE GONE.
BUT WHERE DID ALL THOSE
WOMEN GO?
AAH!
>> [MOANING]
>> AAH!
UHH!
KIRARA!
AAH!
>> SANGO!
SANGO!
WHERE COULD SHE BE?
>> I LOSE SANGO'S SCENT
RIGHT HERE.
SHE MIGHT HAVE GONE INTO
THE WATER FOR ALL WE KNOW.
HUH?
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> OH, NO--
KAGOME, GET BACK!
>> THE VILLAGE WOMEN.
>> HEY, YOU, WHAT'D YOU DO
WITH SANGO?
IF YOU HID HER SOMEWHERE,
YOU BETTER TELL ME.
>> INUYASHA, WAIT!
THERE'S SOME KIND OF
DEMONIC VAPOR SEEPING OUT
OF THEIR MOUTHS.
>> OH!
>> THEY'RE BEING CONTROLLED
BY SOMETHING OR SOMEONE.
WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T HURT
THEM.
>> UHH!
>> HMM, SO THIS IS THE VILLAGE
OF DEMON WOMEN WE WERE
LOOKING FOR ALL ALONG.
AND WE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW IT.
>> PLEASE COMFORT ME, MONK,
IT'S BEEN SO LONG.
>> DEMONIC AURA...
IS THERE SOMETHING INSIDE
HER BELLY?
AWW, GEEZ.
JUST MY LUCK, TOO.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
YOU'RE POSSESSED.
AND I THINK I KNOW
WHO'S BEHIND THIS.
TELL ME, WHAT KIND OF DEMON
ARE YOU?
>> HA HA HA...I WANT YOUR FLESH,
GIVE ME YOUR FLESH!
>> MY FLESH?
>> SO, YOU'RE CONSCIOUS?
>> AAH!
WHERE AM I?
>> AND NOW WE SHALL MAKE YOU
ONE OF US.
>> WHAT IS THAT THING?
IT LOOKS LIKE A KIND OF EGG.
>> HERE, SWALLOW IT.
>> YOU MUST SWALLOW IT
WITHOUT BITING, AND VERY SOON
THE EGG WILL HATCH INSIDE
YOUR STOMACH AND YOU, TOO,
SHALL BECOME ONE OF US.
>> NO WAY, YOU'RE NOT GONNA
MAKE ME SWALLOW THAT THING.
>> OHH...OHH.
>> TRAPPED IN A VILLAGE
OF DEMON WOMEN,
SANGO IS PUT UNDER A SPELL
AND ATTACKS MIROKU.
NO!
WHY DO YOU TWO HAVE TO FIGHT?
>> THEY MUST HAVE MADE HER
SWALLOW A DEMON.
I GUESS THIS WON'T BE AS EASY
AS DEALING WITH THE WOMEN
FROM THE VILLAGE.
SANGO, YOU'RE ONE PERSON I
WOULDN'T WANT TO MAKE AN ENEMY.
BUT I CAN'T JUST SIT HERE
AND LET YOU KILL ME.
>> NEXT TIME,
MIROKU'S MOST DANGEROUS
CONFESSION.
>> YOU'RE A VERY SPECIAL WOMAN
TO ME.