>> NARAKU IS ON THE VERGE OF
COMPLETING THE SACRED JEWEL.
LEARNING THAT FACT, WE CONTINUE
OUR JOURNEY TO FIND THE
REMAINING SHARDS OF THE
SHIKON JEWEL.
WHO'D HAVE GUESSED THAT DURING
OUR TRAVELS WE'D COME UPON THAT
OLD WOMAN AGAIN.
>> HAH.
FOUL DEMONS, AWAY WITH YOU.
>> IT'S NOT REALLY MUCH OF
A DINNER, IS IT?
>> WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO LIVE
WITH IT, THE BIG FISH WEREN'T
BITING.
>> ARE YOU ALL OUT OF YOUR NINJA
FOOD, KAGOME?
>> ALL GONE.
>> MIROKU, WHY DIDN'T YOU STOCK
UP MORE FOOD?
>> I WOULD HAVE IF WE'D HAD THE
MONEY TO PAY FOR IT.
>> YOU MEAN, WE'RE ALL OUT
OF MONEY?
>> YES.
SO WHETHER WE LIKE IT OR NOT,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO EARN SOME
MONEY ALONG THE WAY.
HUH?
[STOMACH GROWLS]
>> HUH?
>> UHH.
>> WELL, LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
DONE.
[SQUEAKS]
>> LET'S DIG IN.
>> OH!
>> YEAH!
>> [GROWLS]
LOOK, SHIPPO, I'M BIGGER THAN
YOU, SO I'M HUNGRIER.
>> BUT I'M A GROWING BOY SO I
NEED MORE FOOD THAN YOU.
AH!
>> GOT IT.
>> HEY, THAT'S MIN--
OHH--UHH.
>> AS IF YOU COULD EVER WIN
AGAINST ME, SHIPPO, THAT'LL
BE THE DAY.
>> INUYASHA--
SIT, BOY!
>> I GOT IT!
>> AS IF.
MM, THAT HIT THE SPOT.
>> [CRIES]
>> WE'LL BE ABLE TO EAT OUR FILL
TOMORROW, SHIPPO.
>> UH-HUH.
STUPID INUYASHA, JUST YOU WAIT.
I'LL GET BACK AT YOU FOR TAKING
WHAT'S MINE.
>> PLEASE REMEMBER,
WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU,
MADAME EXORCIST.
>> YES.
YOU JUST LEAVE EVERYTHING TO ME,
OK?
>> THIS WIND SEEMS OMINOUS.
>> COME NOW, IT'S A LITTLE GUST,
NOTHING MORE.
>> OHH.
>> IT STRUCK AGAIN!
>> HUH?
>> MADAME EXORCIST!
OHH.
MADAME EXORCIST, WE'VE BEEN
ROBBED AGAIN.
>> AH, IT APPEARS I WAS
MISTAKEN.
HE STRUCK A DIFFERENT HOUSE
THIS NIGHT.
>> HMM.
THIS SEEMS TO BE QUITE A
CHEERFUL LITTLE TOWN.
>> IS SOMETHING WRONG WITH THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF WE'LL BE ABLE
TO FIND ANY HOUSES IN NEED OF
SUTURE CHARMS OR EXORCISMS.
>> DOESN'T MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE
SINCE YOUR CHARMS AND EXORCISMS
ARE FAKE ANYWAY.
>> THAT MAY OR MAY NOT BE, BUT
IF THERE IS NO THREAT OF EVIL
DEMONS, THEN I CANNOT APPLY MY
SPIRITUAL SERVICES.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, YOUR
SPIRITUAL SERVICES?
>> HE SHOULD NOT BE PROUD OF
WHAT HE'S SAYING.
>> AT ANY RATE, IF WE CAN'T MAKE
ANY MONEY, THEN WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO SLEEP AT AN INN TONIGHT.
>> COME ON, WHAT'S WRONG WITH
SLEEPING OUTDOORS?
>> I WANT TO TAKE A NICE STEAMY
BATH AND SLEEP IN A BED.
>> I WANNA EAT SOME DECENT FOOD,
IF YOU DON'T STEAL IT.
>> DECENT FOOD WOULD BE NICE.
>> [GRUMBLES]
SO WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO
ABOUT IT.
>> HELLO THERE.
>> HUH?
>> HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN A WHILE,
HOW HAVE YOU ALL BEEN?
>> HEY, IT'S HER.
>> THE EXORCIST.
>> HMM, DEMONIC AURA, HUH?
MM.
MM, WELL I DON'T SENSE ANYTHING
AT ALL.
>> HOW ODD.
>> SOME EXORCIST YOU ARE.
>> UH!
OVER HERE, OVER HERE.
>> WAIT, I SAY!
OFF WITH YOU, DEMON!
>> NO WAY.
>> SIT!
>> WHAT?
UHH.
>> WILL YOU TWO GIVE IT A REST
ALREADY?
>> YOU STILL HAVE MUCH TO STUDY
IN THE LESSONS OF LIFE.
>> WHAT?
YOU FAKE EXORCIST.
>> WELL, I'M NOT SURE ABOUT HER
ABILITY AS AN EXORCIST, BUT
SHE'S PRETTY SHARP AS A WOMAN.
>> YOU MUST HAVE BEEN QUITE
WORRIED...
KNOWING THAT THE MONK AND THE
PRINCESS WERE IN EACH OTHER'S
ARMS.
YOU'RE VERY FOND OF HIM, I CAN
TELL THE MONK MEANS QUITE A LOT
TO YOU.
IT'S WRITTEN ALL OVER YOUR FACE.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE THAT,
OLD WOMAN.
WHERE DID SHE GO?
>> HURRY IT UP, OR I'LL LEAVE
YOU BEHIND.
>> EHH...
[SQUEAKS]
>> YOU SEEM TO BE DOING VERY
WELL, MADAME EXORCIST.
>> OH, I'M JUST FINE.
AND THAT'S WHY I CAN STILL
PURSUE MY WORK AS AN EXORCIST,
YOU SEE.
>> SHE'S STILL DOING EXORCISMS?
>> HOW ON EARTH DOES SHE MANAGE
TO STAY ALIVE?
>> I'M VERY GLAD THAT YOU'VE
COME BECAUSE I NEED A LITTLE
HELP WITH A CERTAIN JOB.
AND I CAN THINK OF NO ONE BETTER
THAN YOU FINE FOLKS TO HELP ME
WITH IT.
>> IS THERE SOME PROFIT TO BE
MADE HERE?
>> YES, THE LATEST JOB HAS BEEN
MORE TROUBLE THAN I HAD
ANTICIPATED AND I WAS
CONSIDERING GETTING MORE HELP.
>> THEN LET US HEAR YOU OUT,
GOOD WOMAN.
>> THERE HAVE BEEN MYSTERIOUS
HAPPENINGS IN THE NIGHT.
ONLY THE HOMES OF THE WEALTHY
ARE TARGETED.
NO MATTER HOW TIGHT THE
SECURITY, SOMEBODY OR SOMETHING
MANAGES TO BREAK INTO THE HOUSE
AND STEAL EVERYTHING OF VALUE.
BECAUSE OF THE MYSTERIOUS
CIRCUMSTANCES OF THE ROBBERIES,
RUMOR HAS IT THAT A DEMON IS
RESPONSIBLE FOR THESE
EVIL DEEDS.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, MYSTERIOUS
CIRCUMSTANCES?
>> THE HOUSE CAN BE LOCKED UP
TIGHT, BUT SOMEHOW THE THIEF
STILL MANAGES TO ENTER.
AND, THOUGH SOMETIMES AN OMINOUS
PRESENCE IS FELT, NOTHING IS
EVER SEEN.
PEOPLE ARE SAYING THAT THIS
THIEF CAN WALK THROUGH WALLS AND
BECOME INVISIBLE.
>> JUST LIKE A NINJA.
>> IMPOSSIBLE, EVEN FOR A NINJA.
>> THEN DOES THAT MEAN THIS
THING CAN REALLY WALK THROUGH
WALLS AND BECOME INVISIBLE?
>> LOGIC DOES SUGGEST THAT IF
IT'S NOT THE WORK OF A HUMAN,
THEN IT MUST BE A DEMON.
>> I'LL BE ABLE TO SEE THROUGH
HIS TRICKS.
'CAUSE THIS INVISIBLE ENEMY IS
UNDOUBTEDLY USING DEMON MAGIC.
>> AH, COME ON, GIVE IT A REST,
SHIPPO.
MAYBE YOU CAN SEE THROUGH HIS
TRICKS, BUT I'LL SNIFF HIM OUT
FIRST.
>> YOU GIVE IT A REST, YOU'RE
ALWAYS BEING SUCKERED IN BY
DEMON MAGIC.
>> WHATEVER, THE ONLY MAGIC YOU
PERFORM IS TO RUN AWAY.
>> SHUT UP, THAT'S NOT TRUE!
>> AND FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
I LET MYSELF GET TRICKED ON
PURPOSE.
>> STOP IT, YOU TWO, RIGHT THIS
MINUTE.
>> HUH.
>> HEY, WHERE'S MIROKU GOING?
>> WHEN YOU'VE SORTED THINGS OUT
YOU CAN FOLLOW US, OK?
THIS IS THE TOWN'S SECOND
RICHEST HOUSEHOLD.
>> OH?
>> BOTH THE RICHEST AND SECOND
RICHEST HOMES HAVE BEEN ROBBED
ALREADY, AND I'VE BEEN EMPLOYED
BY THEM BOTH, SO RATHER THAN
MAKE THE SAME MISTAKES, I WANT
TO BREAK UP INTO 2 GROUPS AND
STAKE OUT EACH HOUSE.
>> THAT SEEMS REASONABLE.
HOW DO YOU WANT TO DIVIDE US UP?
>> I REFUSE TO TEAM UP WITH
INUYASHA.
>> HMM.
DAMN RIGHT, I DON'T NEED YOU
ANYWAY.
>> INUYASHA WILL JUST END UP
BEING TRICKED BY DEMON MAGIC
AGAIN.
>> SHUT UP, SHORT STUFF.
I'LL CUT DOWN THE CRIMINAL WITH
MY WIND SCAR.
>> UHH, OHH.
>> STOP IT, INUYASHA!
>> MIROKU AND I MUST WORK
SEPARATELY SINCE WE BOTH USE
SPIRITUAL POWERS.
>> HUH?
>> RIGHT, SPIRITUAL POWERS.
SANGO, CAN YOU WATCH OVER MY
ESTEEMED SPIRITUAL PEER?
>> NO PROBLEM, COME ON, KIRARA.
>> ALL RIGHT THEN, THE OTHER
GIRL GOES WITH THE MONK.
>> SO I GUESS I'M ON MIROKU'S
TEAM.
>> MIROKU WILL PROBABLY BE MUCH
MORE EFFECTIVE THAN THE
OLD WOMAN.
>> EVEN MIROKU'S MORE USEFUL
THAN THAT OLD HAG.
>> IF INUYASHA GOES WITH THE
OTHER GROUP, THERE WON'T BE
ANYONE THERE TO KEEP HIM
IN LINE.
>> MY SENTIMENTS EXACTLY.
SHIPPO?
I THINK IT WOULD BE BEST IF YOU
WERE TO HELP THE EXORCIST WITH
YOUR FOX DEMON MAGIC.
>> WHAT--ME HELP THE OLD WOMAN?
>> AND DON'T COME RUNNING BACK
TO US.
>> HUH, I'LL USE MY FOX DEMON
MAGIC TO CATCH THIS BANDIT.
>> WELL, THAT'S ALL SETTLED
THEN.
I'LL LEAVE YOU IN CHARGE OF THIS
HOUSE, MIROKU.
WE'RE OFF TO THE TOWN'S FIRST
RICHEST HOUSE.
>> PLEASE TRY TO HELP US.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
DO?
>> OK, WELL, THIS DEMON OR
WHATEVER THE HECK IT IS ONLY
STRIKES AT NIGHT, RIGHT?
SO, WE WAIT FOR IT.
>> RIGHT.
SO WE SHOULD REST AND SAVE OUR
STRENGTH FOR LATER.
>> DO YOU THINK IT WOULD BE
ALL RIGHT TO ASK FOR A BATH?
>> DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
>> IF YOU TELL THEM IT'S IN
PREPARATION FOR TONIGHT,
I'M SURE THEY WON'T OBJECT.
RELAX AND ENJOY YOURSELF.
[LAUGHS]
>> I WONDER IF SHIPPO AND THE
OTHERS ARE ALL RIGHT.
>> I BEG OF YOU, DO YOUR BEST
TO HELP US.
>> THAT MAN SEEMS SO DEPRESSED.
>> WELL, IT'S NO WONDER HE'S
DEPRESSED, HIS HOUSE MAY BE
BROKEN INTO TONIGHT.
>> SO, THEN, WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO NOW?
>> OH, I HAD A FEW IDEAS
ABOUT--LOOK!
THE TEA LEAF IS STANDING UP.
THAT IS A GOOD OMEN.
>> WHAT KIND OF IDEAS?
>> TELL ME, DO YOU REALLY KNOW
HOW TO USE DEMON MAGIC?
>> OF COURSE I DO.
>> AND CAN YOU DISAPPEAR, TOO?
>> I CAN'T ACTUALLY DISAPPEAR AS
SUCH, BUT I'VE HEARD OF DEMON
MAGIC LIKE THAT.
>> I'VE NEVER HEARD OF A DEMON
WHO COULD BECOME INVISIBLE
BEFORE.
>> NEITHER HAVE I, ALTHOUGH I DO
HAVE A TALISMAN THAT CAN CONCEAL
ONE'S PRESENCE.
>> CHECK IT OUT, I HAVE A TRICK
LIKE THAT, TOO.
>> IF THE ENEMY CAN HIDE ITSELF,
THEN WE SHALL DO THE SAME AND
HIDE OURSELVES.
>> HMM.
>> HMM, SHALL WE TRY COMBINING
THEM?
>> WHOA, GOOD IDEA, IT'S WORTH
A TRY AT LEAST.
HERE'S A LITTLE FOX MAGIC.
HIDDEN CLOUD!
>> OH!
>> HOW WAS THAT?
>> JUST THE TAIL, MY BOY.
>> ONCE MORE.
>> OH!
HE DID IT!
>> IT ACTUALLY WORKS.
>> HOW WAS IT THAT TIME?
>> NOTHING LEFT.
>> COULDN'T SEE A THING.
>> HA HA, YES!
I, SHIPPO, NOW POSSESS THE POWER
OF INVISIBILITY.
HEH HEH HEH.
>> RIGHT.
LET'S TRY IT ON OTHER THINGS
NOW.
>> UHH, YOU SURE?
>> FOX MAGIC!
HIDDEN CLOUD!
I'VE PERFECTED THE HIDDEN CLOUD
TECHNIQUE.
>> THAT WAS AMAZING.
>> HUH?
HEY, WAIT.
HEH HEH HEH.
I NEED TO GO DO SOMETHING BEFORE
WE CAPTURE THIS DEMON, OK?
>> OH!
>> I'LL BE BACK BY SUNDOWN.
>> WHERE IS HE GOING?
WHAT COULD BE SO IMPORTANT?
>> UMM, I HAVE TO GO OUT, TOO.
>> HUH, WHAT DID YOU SAY?
[SQUEAKS]
>> THEY'RE LOVELY, HOW MUCH FOR
THIS GOURD?
>> HA HA HA!
>> THAT'S MINE!
>> HERE, CATCH.
>> GIVE IT BACK!
>> COME ON.
HA HA HA.
>> IF YOU WANT IT BACK YOU'VE
GOTTA TURN AROUND 3 TIMES.
[LAUGHS]
[SQUEAKS]
>> HEY, CUT IT OUT, YOU TWO.
>> HUH?
>> GIVE IT BACK TO HER.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT,
A TALKING CAT.
AAH!
IT'S A DEMON CAT.
>> LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
>> AAH!
>> HUH?
[SQUEAKS]
>> HERE YOU GO.
BYE-BYE.
>> THANK YOU, NICE LADY.
>> OH, STOP IT, MONK.
>> NO, NO, I'M DEAD SERIOUS,
GIRLS, BELIEVE ME.
>> REALLY?
>> OH, YOU HAVE MY WORD.
HUH?
>> THEN SAY IT ONCE MORE.
>> WOULD YOU LADIES CARE TO BEAR
MY CHILDREN?
>> OH, MY GOODNESS!
>> OH, NO, SHE SAW ME.
OK, MIROKU, THINK, MONK, THINK.
>> WHY EVER DID YOU CHOOSE US TO
BE YOUR PARAMOURS?
>> UH, WELL, I SUPPOSE IT WAS
YOUR HIPS.
>> HMM?
>> OH!
OH!
>> NO, LET'S SAVE THAT FOR
LATER.
>> HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT, SHE WOULD
NORMALLY HAVE INTERVENED BY NOW.
WHY--WHY IS SHE SO SILENT?
WHY DOES SHE FOLLOW ME WITHOUT
A WORD?
AND WHAT IS THAT SUTURE ON HER
FOREHEAD?
OH!
IS IT MEANT AS SOME KIND OF
MESSAGE FOR ME?
>> COME NOW, MONK.
>> WHY ARE YOU SO SILENT ALL
OF A SUDDEN?
>> WELL, I'M SPEECHLESS BECAUSE
I'M SURROUNDED BY SUCH PRETTY
WOMEN.
>> OH, STOP.
>> HURRY, HURRY, AND LASH OUT
AT ME.
WHY ARE YOU ACTING SO STRANGELY?
>> SIT HERE, MONK.
>> WHICH ONE OF US DO YOU THINK
IS PRETTIER?
>> UHH.
PLEASE, GO EASY ON ME, SANGO.
>> HUH?
>> I KNOW I'VE MISBEHAVED AND
I DESERVE TO BE PUNISHED.
>> YOU--YOU CAN SEE ME?
>> AND WHAT OF THAT STRANGE
SUTURE ON YOUR FOREHEAD?
IT'S DIRECTED AT ME SOMEHOW,
I KNOW THAT IT IS.
OHH.
>> UMM, MIROKU?
YOU CAN REALLY SEE ME?
>> OF COURSE I CAN, THOUGH I
KNOW I DON'T DESERVE TO.
>> BUT--THEN--
ALL THIS TIME, OH--
>> HUH?
SANGO, WAIT!
>> HMM?
>> HEE HEE HEE.
>> THAT SHIPPO.
I WONDER WHAT HE'S UP TO NOW.
>> [SNORES]
HUH?
>> HA HA HA.
>> HMM.
HE'S FINALLY LOST IT.
[GROWLS]
>> AAH!
OHH.
UHH.
>> HEY, SHIPPO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO
YOU, BUT NOBODY GETS AWAY
WITH THAT.
>> AAH!
>> DAMN THAT SHIPPO.
HE STEALS MY FOOD, STUFFS IT UP
MY NOSE, AND THEN KICKS ME IN
THE HEAD WITH A DUMB GRIN ON HIS
FACE.
>> WELL, IT MAKES SENSE.
YOU TWO ARE REALLY CLOSE.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS OBVIOUS.
YOU AND SHIPPO FIGHT SO MUCH
'CAUSE YOU'RE SO CLOSE TO EACH
OTHER.
BUT SHIPPO'S A LOT SMALLER THAN
YOU, SO GO EASY ON HIM, OK?
>> OH, I'LL GO EASY ON HIM.
HUH.
>> HMM, THAT WAS CARELESS OF ME.
INUYASHA HAS A KEEN SENSE OF
SMELL, HE MUST HAVE CAUGHT MY
SCENT OR SOMETHING.
>> HMM, LET'S HOPE THAT THE
INVISIBLE DEMON DOESN'T HAVE A
SHARP NOSE OR WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
>> UH, SHIPPO?
>> YES, WHAT IS IT, SANGO?
>> OH...IT'S NOTHING.
>> IT WILL BE DARK SOON.
WE'VE BEEN ASKED TO GUARD THIS
FAMILY'S HEIRLOOM--A PRECIOUS
ANCIENT SCROLL.
>> AN OLD SCROLL?
>> FOR SOME REASON, THE DEMON
HAS BEEN STEALING SCROLLS ON
ROLLS OF SILK.
>> HMM.
>> SO, WE'VE ALL HAD OUR DINNER.
>> AND TAKEN A BATH.
>> NOW ALL THAT'S LEFT IS TO
WAIT FOR THE CULPRIT TO APPEAR.
>> I WONDER IF HE'LL SHOW UP.
>> YEAH, WHAT IF HE DOESN'T
SHOW UP?
>> WE WAIT.
>> SO DO ALL 3 OF US HAVE TO
STAY UP ALL NIGHT?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
KAGOME, WHY DON'T YOU GO GET
SOME SLEEP IN THE NEXT ROOM?
>> THANKS, BUT I'D LIKE TO STAY
UP AS LONG AS I CAN.
>> IT MAY NOT BE THIS HOUSE
TONIGHT.
>> SO, I WONDER WHEN AND WHERE
THE DEMON WILL APPEAR?
>> DID YOU JUST SENSE SOMETHING?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
>> HUH?
UH, ALL RIGHT.
I GUESS SHE WOULDN'T.
BY THE WAY, WHERE'S SHIPPO?
>> HE MADE HIMSELF INVISIBLE AND
IS WAITING BACK AT THE HOUSE.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T WORRY, EVEN IF THAT
DEMON WERE TO SHOW UP, SHIPPO
CAN'T BE SEEN SO HE'S SAFE.
>> SHIPPO.
>> HUH?
>> AAH!
OOH, OOH.
>> OH, WELL.
HUH?
WHOA...OHH, HO HO HO.
OOH, OOH.
>> WHOA!
UH.
NO!
THE HANGING SCROLLS!
FOX FIRE!
>> OH!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
>> UH, WHAT--ARE YOU SAYING YOU
CAN ACTUALLY SEE ME?
HUH?
THIS IS BAD.
SANGO, OLD WOMAN!
>> HUH?
>> WHOA...OH!
>> HUH.
>> AAH!
>> HMM?
OHH!
>> HOW DID THIS GIGANTIC DEMON
MANAGE TO GET INSIDE THE HOUSE?
>> HEY, HE'S NOT INVISIBLE
AT ALL.
>> GIVE THEM TO ME.
GIVE ME BACK THE TREASURES
I FOUND.
>> HE'S GONE.
>> HE IS INVISIBLE, AFTER ALL.
>> BUT HE HASN'T DISAPPEARED.
>> HAND THEM OVER TO ME.
>> AAH!
>> HEY, WHERE THE BLAZES
ARE YOU?
DAMN DEMON, SHOW YOURSELF!
>> GIVE ME THE TREASURES!
>> SHIPPO, WHY ARE YOU STUMBLING
AROUND?
>> INUYASHA.
>> I SEE--YOU'RE TRYING TO
PROTECT THE TREASURES.
AND THAT MEANS--
>> DO YOU SEE HIM?
>> YUP.
I SEE YOU.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY.
UH!
>> BUT--BUT HOW?
>> YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE HERE WITH
AN UNFAMILIAR SCENT.
>> HEY!
>> INUYASHA.
>> WELL, WE CAUGHT HIM, BUT WHAT
DO WE DO WITH HIM NOW?
>> PLEASE, PLEASE, SPARE ME.
>> ON ONE CONDITION.
>> HUH?
>> RETURN EVERY SINGLE THING
YOU'VE STOLEN.
>> THINGS THAT ARE THIN AND
SHINY ATTRACT ME, SO I COULDN'T
HELP MYSELF.
>> THERE'S SO MUCH.
>> SHOULD WE DIVIDE UP
THE SPOILS?
>> EVERYTHING GOES BACK TO ITS
OWNERS.
>> OH, WELL, I'M SURE WE'LL BE
RICHLY REWARDED.
>> I ALMOST HAD MY NEW FOX MAGIC
TRICK WORKED OUT PERFECTLY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, NEW FOX
MAGIC?
>> WELL, IT'S A LITTLE SOMETHING
I DISCOVERED EARLIER.
YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
>> YEAH.
>> NOW THAT YOU'VE LEARNED YOUR
LESSON, PLEASE STAY AWAY FROM
HUMANS.
>> YES, THANK YOU.
>> WOW, HE'S PAPER THIN.
>> SO, WHEN HE TURNS SIDEWAYS,
HE APPEARS INVISIBLE.
>> I WAS SO TERRIFIED, I REALLY
THOUGHT THAT I'D FINALLY SEEN
THIS INVISIBLE DEMON.
>> OH, COME ON, ARE YOU STUPID,
SHIPPO?
>> I AM NOT STUPID.
>> IF IT WAS INVISIBLE,
YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO SEE IT.
>> OH, RIGHT.
>> AKITOKI OF THE HOJO FAMILY
CAME TO US WITH A PROBLEM.
IT SEEMS HE'S ON ANOTHER JOURNEY
TO SEAL AWAY SOMETHING CALLED
THE NAGINATA OF KENKON.
>> AND HE'S THE ANCESTOR TO THE
HOJO I KNOW IN MY TIME.
I SAW IN THEIR FAMILY TREE THAT
THERE'S A GIRL NAMED KAGOME
ON THERE.
CAN IT BE THAT I STAY IN THE
PAST, AND I GET MARRIED TO
AKITOKI?
>> NEXT TIME, ON "INUYASHA."
AN ANCESTOR NAMED KAGOME.
HEY, I SENSE A STORM COMING.