- SESSHOMARU, DESPISING
THE HUMAN RACE.
HE HAD DENOUNCED INUYASHA,
THE HALF-DEMON,
AS A DISGRACE TO HIS CLAN.
SO WHY DID SESSHOMARU'S
HENCHMAN, JAKEN,
HAVE A HUMAN GIRL
ACCOMPANYING HIM?
- KNIGHT SESSHOMARU!
[PANTING]
RIN HAS BEEN ABDUCTED!
NARAKU'S INCARNATION, KAGURA,
APPEARED OUT OF NOWHERE
AND TOOK OFF WITH RIN!
- LET ME REASSURE YOU,
SESSHOMARU.
[INSECTS BUZZING]
IF YOU HEED MY REQUEST,
I SHALL RETURN RIN
IN GOOD HEALTH.
- AAH!
IT'S NARAKU!
[LAUGHS]
- JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
SOON YOU WILL BE
ABSORBED INTO MY BODY,
AND YOU WILL BE
ONE WITH MY FLESH.
- WE FOLLOWED THE TRAIL
LEADING TO A SACRED JEWEL SHARD,
WHICH MIGHT JUST LEAD US TO
SANGO'S BROTHER KOHAKU,
SEEING AS NARAKU HAD EMBEDDED
A SHARD IN HIS BACK.
MEANWHILE, INUYASHA HEADS TO
NARAKU'S CASTLE ON HIS OWN.
- THAT HYPNOTIC AURA
AND TOXIC GASES?
THIS HAS GOT TO BE
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
I'M SURE OF IT.
TETSUSAIGA!
THERE IT IS.
NARAKU'S CASTLE!
[CHUCKLES]
- HUH?
HE'S HEADED THIS WAY.
KAGURA MUST HAVE FAILED.
- NARAKU
- HMM?
- YOU SEEM PREOCCUPIED WITH
WHAT'S OUTSIDE THESE WALLS.
- LORD SESSHOMARU,
I AM AFRAID THAT I'LL
HAVE TO CUT OUR VISIT SHORT.
I WILL HAVE YOUR POWER,
EVERY LAST BIT
OF YOUR DEMONIC POWER.
I SHALL HAVE IT ALL FOR MYSELF.
[CHUCKLES]
[WHIMPERING]
- IT'S SESSHOMARU!
[SCREAMING]
THIS IS TERRIBLE!
- STOP THAT, YOU HEADS!
[SCREAMING]
- OH, NO!
IT DIDN'T WORK! HELP!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[THUNDER]
[WHIMPERING]
- HUH?
CAN HE SAVE HIMSELF?
AAH! I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
MY LORD HAS BEEN ENGULFED!
OH...A DEATH TOO CRUEL.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[LAUGHS]
- AT LAST I HAVE ATTAINED
THE FULL POWERS
OF A COMPLETE DEMON.
- NARAKU!
- HUH?
- NO WONDER YOU'VE BEEN HIDING
YOUR TRUE FORM.
- INUYASHA.
- YOU'RE DEAD!
WIND SCAR!
- I THINK NOT.
[SCREAMING]
[MOANING]
HE'S BROKEN THROUGH MY BARRIER.
- UHH.
I FOUND YOU, NARAKU,
AND TODAY,
I'M GONNA DESTROY YOU.
- HA. DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN SLAY ME?
- HE CAN.
INUYASHA'S STRONG ENOUGH NOW.
[GASPS]
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
NARAKU HAS ALREADY ENGULFED
SESSHOMARU'S BODY.
THEN NARAKU MUST BE DEFEATED
BEFORE HE'S HAD
A CHANCE TO ABSORB
SESSHOMARU'S DEMONIC POWER.
[THUNDER]
- MY MISTAKE.
I NEVER EXPECTED INUYASHA
TO GET THIS FAR.
[CHUCKLES]
INUYASHA, YOU'VE GROWN
STRONG ENOUGH
TO BREAK THROUGH MY BARRIER.
- UHH.
NARAKU, YOU BASTARD,
YOU WON'T ESCAPE THIS TIME.
PREPARE TO DIE!
- HA. YOU MAY HAVE
GROWN MORE POWERFUL,
BUT YOU ARE CERTAINLY
NO MATCH FOR ME.
NOW, PERISH!
[GRUNTING]
- NOT THIS TIME!
UHH!
- I'M NOT DONE WITH YOU YET.
- OH, YEAH?
NARAKU.
[SCREAMING]
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
WHAT?
[CHUCKLING]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
I'M ENGULFING
BODY AND SOUL,
JUST LIKE I DID
WITH SESSHOMARU.
- WHAT?
SESSHOMARU?
[GRUNTING]
- I WAS WRONG.
NARAKU'S STILL TOO STRONG
FOR HIM.
- YOU'RE TOO LATE, INUYASHA.
I HAVE ALREADY CONSUMED
SESSHOMARU.
I DON'T KNOW THAT
YOUR HALF-DEMON POWER
WILL DO ME ANY GOOD.
BUT STILL, I WILL ABSORB
YOUR BODY INTO MY FLESH.
- DON'T ASSUME I'M AS WEAK
AS SESSHOMARU.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
HUH?
- THIS IS THE END, NARAKU!
YOU'RE GOING DOWN THIS TIME!
NOW, DIE!
UHH!
[GASP]
- AAH!
IT'S SESSHOMARU!
[SOBBING]
- SESSHOMARU!
- HUH?
MY LORD, YOU'RE ALIVE!
- HUH. NARAKU.
IRONIC, ISN'T IT,
TO THINK THAT THE FLESH
THAT BOUND ME TO YOU
WOULD BE YOUR SHIELD
AGAINST INUYASHA'S WIND SCAR.
- MOVE IT.
I'M TAKING NARAKU DOWN.
- NO.
NARAKU BELONGS TO ME.
- HUH!
NOT LIKELY.
THIS TIME YOU WON'T INTERFERE.
[RUMBLING]
I SHALL ABSORB BOTH OF YOU...
WHAT'S THAT?
[LAUGHS]
- DIE!
[GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
- YOU CANNOT ESCAPE
MY ATTACKS FOREVER.
- JUST DIE, WILL YA?
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
- THIS SHOULD FINISH YOU OFF
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
UHH.
ONE MORE SHOULD DO IT.
HUH?
- I TOLD YOU TO LET ME TAKE HIM.
- BACK DOWN.
- UHH.
[GRUNTING]
- HUH?
THE MIASMA.
[BUZZING]
- LORD SESSHOMARU,
I SHALL WITHDRAW FOR NOW.
[GRUMBLES]
- HUH?
- YOU FOOL!
DON'T THINK THAT YOU CAN EVER
ESCAPE MY GRASP.
[CHUCKLES]
- LORD SESSHOMARU,
RATHER THAN TRANSFORMING
AND HUNTING ME DOWN,
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
RUSHING TO THE SIDE
OF THAT YOUNG MORTAL GIRL?
- HUH?
KOHAKU?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WHAT MORTAL GIRL?
WHO'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
- YOUR COMPANION, RIN,
IS WITH A BOY NAMED KOHAKU.
HUH? KOHAKU?
- INUYASHA, EVEN YOU
SHOULD REALIZE THE IMPLICATIONS.
[CHUCKLES]
- KOHAKU?
- I WAS SO CLOSE
TO GAINING CONTROL
OF SESSHOMARU'S
FULL DEMONIC POWER,
AND I WOULD'VE SUCCEEDED
IF ONLY I HADN'T MISCALCULATED
INUYASHA'S POWER.
- NARAKU HAS VANISHED,
AND SO HAS
MY CHANCE FOR FREEDOM.
- HUH.
HE'S GONE.
HIS SCENT AND EVERY TRACE
OF HIS WHEREABOUTS.
HE WAS BADLY INJURED, TOO.
WHERE COULD HE BE?
- HEY, SESSHOMARU.
DID NARAKU TAKE SOMEBODY
AS A HOSTAGE?
A FRIEND OF YOURS NAMED RIN?
- HMM. SO THAT'S WHY
HE ABDUCTED HER,
IN ORDER TO BUY TIME TO ESCAPE.
NARAKU. HE THINKS
HE'S SO CUNNING.
- WAIT!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- HMM?
AAH!
NO, LORD SESSHOMARU!
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND!
ACK!
AAH!
WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH ME?
- I WANT SOME ANSWERS,
WHAT ELSE?
WHAT IS GOING ON BETWEEN
NARAKU AND SESSHOMARU?
- I'M UNDER NO OBLIGATION
TO SPEAK TO
A HALF-DEMON LIKE YOU.
I MEANT,
IT'S A TERRIBLY LONG STORY.
- THEN MAKE IT SHORT.
- HERE COME THE DEMONS.
- UHH.
HIRAIKOTSU! YAA!
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
- OH, NOW I UNDERSTAND.
THEY DON'T WANT US
TO GET NEAR THAT HOUSE.
- HUH?
- WE WERE THERE.
IT IS KOHAKU.
HE'S WITH A LITTLE GIRL.
I KNOW HER.
I'VE SEEN HER SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
- KOHAKU!
DAMN YOU!
OUT OF MY WAY! UHH!
UHH! UHH!
- LET'S FOLLOW HER.
- KAGOME, LOOK!
[SNARLING]
- OH!
- IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
- INUYASHA.
- KAGOME, KOHAKU WAS HERE,
WASN'T HE?
- YOU CAN PROBABLY
CATCH UP TO HIM.
I CAN SENSE THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD CLOSE BY.
- INUYASHA!
- I'M GOING AHEAD.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY TIME TO LOSE.
UHH.
- KOHAKU'S MIND IS BEING
CONTROLLED BY NARAKU.
- YEAH, AND HE'S PROBABLY
PLANTED A SUGGESTION
IN HIS HEAD,
TO KILL THE HOSTAGE.
NARAKU HAD THE GIRL ABDUCTED
SO THAT HE COULD
BUY HIMSELF SOME TIME
TO ESCAPE FROM SESSHOMARU.
- DO YOU THINK SESSHOMARU
AND THE LITTLE GIRL
MIGHT BE TRAVELING TOGETHER?
- TO SESSHOMARU, HUMANS ARE
NO BETTER THAN INSECTS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'D HAVE
A MORTAL AS A COMPANION.
ONE THING I DO KNOW IS THAT
HE WON'T LET KOHAKU LIVE,
NOT AFTER WHAT NARAKU DID.
SESSHOMARU WILL
KILL THE KID FOR SURE.
- SANGO'S YOUNGER BROTHER
WILL BE KILLED
BY YOUR OLDER BROTHER?
IT'S GOING TO BE A LOUSY FINISH,
NO MATTER HOW THIS ENDS.
- WE HAVE TO TRY
AND GET TO KOHAKU
BEFORE SESSHOMARU FINDS HIM.
- YEAH.
AND THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN STOP SESSHOMARU IS ME.
- KOHAKU, WHY DID WE
LEAVE THE HOUSE?
I SAW SOME PEOPLE OUTSIDE
WHEN WE LEFT.
PLEASE TELL ME
WHERE WE'RE GOING NOW.
KOHAKU, SAY SOMETHING.
[GASP]
HUH?
- KILL HER.
- HUH?
HMM?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, KOHAKU?
AAH!
UHH.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS
TO ME, KOHAKU?
AAH!
- KILL HER.
OH?
YOU TURN YOUR BLADE TOWARD ME?
- KOHAKU!
[FOOTSTEPS]
UHH!
[MOANING]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, YOU FOOL?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[EXHALES]
- SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
SHE'S JUST UNCONSCIOUS,
THAT'S ALL.
[SIGHS]
- WE MADE IT IN TIME.
YOU HEARD HER.
THE GIRL'S NOT HURT,
SO LET THE BOY GO FREE.
- STAY OUT OF THIS, INUYASHA.
IT'S USELESS
TO TRY TO INTERFERE.
THIS BOY SEEMS COMPELLED
BEYOND REASON
TO DIE BY MY HANDS.
- HMM?
- GRR. THIS MUST BE
ANOTHER OF NARAKU'S SUGGESTIONS,
TO ATTACK SESSHOMARU
SO THAT KOHAKU
WOULD DIE IN THE PROCESS.
UHH.
HUH?
- HMM. HOW GENEROUS OF YOU,
DISARMING THE BOY FOR ME.
I HAD NO IDEA YOU HELD
SUCH STRONG FEELINGS
FOR ME, INUYASHA.
- LET'S GET ONE THING STRAIGHT,
SESSHOMARU.
- I'LL KILL YOU
IF YOU DON'T LET HIM GO.
- DON'T DO IT, SESSHOMARU.
- SET THE BOY DOWN.
- THIS BOY.
HE SHOWS NO SIGN OF SUFFERING.
HE KNOWS NO FEAR.
I DESPISE THE LOOK IN HIS EYES.
- HUH?
[WHIMPERING]
HUH? OH, YOU'RE AWAKE.
- HUH?
LORD SESSHOMARU!
HMM?
[SIGH]
WHAT HAPPENED, KOHAKU?
UHH.
- AREN'T YOU GOING AFTER HIM?
HUH?
KAGURA.
- THANK YOU, SESSHOMARU.
THANKS FOR LETTING KOHAKU GO.
- THE BOY WAS TRYING
TO DIE AT MY HANDS.
- YOU MEAN, YOU KNEW THAT?
- IT WAS NARAKU'S DOING,
AND I REFUSE TO PLAY
BY HIS RULES.
- HUH?
[LAUGHS]
- GOOD-BYE.
- SHE'S LEAVING WITH HIM.
- OH, SO KOHAKU RAN OFF AGAIN.
- I'M SORRY.
IF I'D KILLED NARAKU,
KOHAKU MIGHT HAVE BEEN FREED.
- IF ONLY WE COULD'VE
GOTTEN TO HIM IN TIME.
- DON'T APOLOGIZE.
I'M JUST GLAD HE'S ALIVE.
- WHERE COULD NARAKU
HAVE DISAPPEARED TO?
WITH A WOUND THAT SERIOUS,
HE WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO PUT UP
A VERY STRONG BARRIER.
WHERE COULD HE BE?
- DID NARAKU LIFT HIS BARRIER,
LEAVING THE CASTLE VISIBLE?
IN THAT CASE, HE MUST HAVE
ABANDONED IT,
AND HE'S HIDING SOMEWHERE NEW.
STRANGE. UNTIL NOW, I'VE BEEN
ABLE TO SENSE HIS BARRIER.
BUT THIS TIME, IT'S AS IF
HE'S VANISHED INTO THIN AIR,
LEAVING NOT A TRACE BEHIND.
I DON'T LIKE THE LOOKS OF THIS.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- DAMN THAT NARAKU!
WE ALMOST HAD HIM CORNERED.
- ARE YOU SURE THIS IS OK,
THAT I'M BACK IN THE MODERN ERA?
- HEY, KAGOME,
IS IT MY IMAGINATION
OR HAVE WE CHANGED PLACES?
- YOU'RE RIGHT!
HOW ARE WE GONNA
GET THROUGH THE PREVIEW?
- JUST RELAX AND DO IT.
- NEXT TIME,
"GAP BETWEEN THE AGES."
HEY, I AIN'T TAKIN' NO TESTS.
- WHEW.
WE'RE BACK TO NORMAL.