- IMAGINE,
THE GATEWAY TO THE TOMB
DISGUISED AS A PEARL
WITHIN THE RIGHT EYE
OF INUYASHA.
NO WONDER LORD SESSHOMARU
WAS UNABLE TO FIND IT.
OF COURSE,
NOW THAT HE HAS FOUND IT,
THERE'S NO TIME TO WASTE.
TETSUSAIGA,
SWORD OF ULTIMATE POWER!
THE TIME IS NOW, MILORD.
MAKE IT YOUR OWN!
- DO YOU MEAN TO SAY
INUYASHA CAN?
- SESSHOMARU COULDN'T
PULL IT OUT, RIGHT?
IF YOU CAN'T HIT HIM
IN THE BODY,
HIT HIM IN THE EGO.
HURT HIS PRIDE.
- OH, NO!
INUYASHA IS IMMUNE TO THE SPELL
THAT THWARTED LORD SESSHOMARU.
- I KNEW IT.
TETSUSAIGA IS MEANT
TO BELONG TO LORD INUYASHA.
- PULL HARDER!
- ARE YOU DONE?
I AM.
- INUYASHA!
[GASPS]
UH-OH.
SORRY.
NOW WHAT?
OH.
[GASPING]
- THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
IF THE TWO OF THEM
COULDN'T DO IT,
HOW COULD A MERE HUMAN
EVER HOPE TO--
- DON'T LOOK AT HER.
LOOK AT ME!
HUH?
[GASPS]
- WHAT ARE YOU,
AND HOW DID YOU
DRAW THE SWORD?
- GOOD THING
HE'S AFTER HER NOW
AND NOT US,
EH, LORD INUYASHA?
- BE QUIET!
SESSHOMARU,
LEAVE HER ALONE!
SHE'S NOT INVOLVED IN THIS.
- INUYASHA!
ONE STEP CLOSER,
AND I'LL CUT YOU.
- FOR SOME UNKNOWN REASON,
I WAS UNABLE
TO DRAW TETSUSAIGA.
FORTUNATELY,
YOU WERE UNABLE
TO DRAW IT EITHER.
IT'S OBVIOUS
THAT SHE MUST DIE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
IT IS WEIRD
SHE COULD DO IT
AND WE COULDN'T,
BUT SHE'S STILL
JUST A HUMAN GIRL.
KAGOME, GIVE HIM THE SWORD.
THERE'S NO CHOICE.
- NO WAY.
WHY DOES HE AUTOMATICALLY
GET TO KEEP IT?
IF HE COULDN'T PULL IT OUT,
IT MEANS HE'S NOT
SUPPOSED TO HAVE IT.
HE'LL HAVE TO
COME AND TAKE IT.
- DON'T BE STUPID.
YOU'RE ONLY A HUMAN,
SO BACK OFF, SHUT UP,
AND BUTT OUT.
- BUTT OUT?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE JUST A--
OOH!
- INUYASHA, YOUR PATIENCE
WITH THIS CREATURE
IS ASTONISHING TO ME.
YOU PROTECT HER,
INDULGE HER--
EVEN SEEM TO LOVE HER.
- UH...
- CERTAINLY THESE
FEELINGS OF MERCY OF YOURS
ARE NOT SOMETHING
I INHERITED FROM OUR GREAT
AND TERRIBLE FATHER.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
THAT MOTHER OF YOURS--
THAT HUMAN MOTHER
WHO CAUSED OUR FATHER
TO MEET HIS END
IN THIS IGNOBLE PLACE.
HER BLOOD AFFECTS YOU
AS WELL.
IS IT THAT WHICH
SO ENDEARS YOU TO THEM?
WHEN IT COMES TO HUMANS,
I, OF COURSE,
BEAR NO SUCH WEAKNESS.
[WHIMPERS]
- INUYASHA!
- KAGOME!
- SO FRAGILE,
DON'T YOU AGREE,
LITTLE BROTHER?
- SESSHOMARU.
- AND NOT JUST HUMANS--
HALF-BREEDS, TOO.
- IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
- HOW CAN YOU THINK
WITH YOUR DIRTY BLOOD
THAT YOU ARE MY EQUAL?
- YOU...
- YOU FORGET YOUR STATION,
WORTHLESS HALF-BREED.
- A HALF-BREED, AM I?
[MEN CHUCKLING]
HALF-BREED?
MOTHER!
WHAT'S A HALF-BREED?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I REMEMBER.
MY MOTHER,
SHE WAS CRYING--
CRYING FOR ME.
SHE KNEW WHAT IT MEANT,
WHAT MY LIFE WOULD BE LIKE.
HALF-BREED OR FULL-BREED,
TO ME IT DON'T MATTER.
BUT WHEN YOU
INSULT MY MOTHER,
THAT'S WHEN I GET ANGRY.
FOR HER SAKE THEN,
IF NOTHING ELSE,
I'M GONNA MAKE YOU PAY.
THAT WAS FOR MOTHER,
AND THIS--
THIS IS FOR KAGOME.
- THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
A MOMENT AGO
HE COULDN'T HIT AT ALL.
- ALL THAT FOR A MEMORY
AND A DEAD MORTAL GIRL?
IF I'D KNOWN
THAT'S WHAT IT TOOK
TO MAKE YOU FIGHT,
I'D HAVE KILLED HER SOONER.
- I'M GONNA SLIT YOUR STOMACH,
TAKE OUT YOUR GUTS,
AND PUT 'EM IN A BOWL.
BY THE TIME I'M THROUGH,
YOU'RE GONNA WISH
IT WAS YOU WHO WAS DEAD.
- I THOUGHT I WAS A GONER.
- HUH?
- HEY, YOU!
YOU TRIED TO KILL ME,
DIDN'T YOU?
DON'T GO THINKING
YOU'RE GONNA GET
AWAY WITH IT, MISTER.
HERE. I THINK
WE UNDERESTIMATED IT.
DON'T LET ME DOWN.
- HEY, UH,
HOW COME YOU'RE STILL ALIVE?
- MMM. UH, I DON'T KNOW.
- THE SWORD--
THAT'S WHAT PROTECTED YOU.
- IT'S TRUE.
THOSE CLAWS OF HIS
ARE DEADLY POISON.
IT HAD TO BE THE SWORD,
OR SHE REALLY WOULD HAVE DIED.
WHY NOT PUT IT TO A REAL TEST
AND TRY IT ON SESSHOMARU?
- BIG WORDS
FOR SUCH SMALL VERMIN.
- WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
WHAT A JERK.
- LET'S SEE IF A HALF-BREED
CAN EVEN WIELD THE TETSUSAIGA.
I MYSELF SHALL BE THE WITNESS.
- HE CHANGED.
- GOOD, 'CAUSE NOW
WE KNOW HIS REAL FORM.
HEH.
HEH HEH.
NOW THAT I'M USING THIS,
I'LL WIN FOR SURE.
- YUP, I'D SAY THIS BATTLE'S
JUST ABOUT FINISHED
BEFORE IT EVEN STARTS.
HA!
YOU GO HIDE
UNTIL IT'S OVER.
- OK, SURE. BUT WHERE?
- HERE GOES.
THIS IS IT, SWORD.
TIME TO SHOW ME
WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF.
- AAH!
- DIDN'T EVEN MAKE A SCRATCH.
HUH?
YO, MYOGA, WHAT'S THE DEAL?
THIS SWORD CAN'T EVEN BRUISE,
LET ALONE CUT.
- WELL, UH, LORD INUYASHA,
I SUPPOSE THAT, UH,
IT'LL MAKE A LOVELY HEIRLOOM
IF NOTHING ELSE.
BESIDES,
IT'S THE THOUGHT
THAT COUNTS.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
- HEY, HEY! WHOA!
- AND DON'T LET THAT SESSHOMARU
PUSH YOU AROUND, OK?
- UH-OH.
KAGOME, QUICK!
GET UP OFF THE GROUND!
- WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
- JUST CLIMB UP.
UP! UP!
- INUYASHA!
- NOW JUST CLIMB!
EVEN A DEMON CAN'T STAY
IN THOSE FUMES FOR LONG.
- LORD SESSHOMARU, I CAN'T--
AAH!
- WHAT ABOUT HIM?
WHAT ABOUT INUYASHA?
WILL HE BE OK?
- UH, PROBABLY NOT, HUH?
FORGET THE HEROICS.
IT'S EVERY FLEA FOR HIMSELF.
COME ON!
- INUYASHA!
[COUGHS]
- EVEN I CAN'T STAY DOWN HERE
TOO MUCH LONGER.
[COUGHS]
MY ARMS AND LEGS
ARE GOING NUMB.
AAH!
EVEN A MOSQUITO
WITH WOODEN TEETH
MUST BITE HARDER
THAN THIS PIECE OF JUNK.
AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- NOW DO YOU SEE
THE POWER OF TETSUSAIGA?
OH, YOU'RE GIVING
SESSHOMARU WHAT FOR, I HOPE.
WOO-HOO!
- WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
THIS THING'S ABOUT AS USEFUL
AS A WALKING STICK!
- OH, SO MAYBE
IT ISN'T FROM YOUR FATHER.
[CLEARS THROAT]
- HEY!
HE LEFT.
- WHY AM I NOT SURPRISED?
IN THE MEANTIME,
WHAT AM I GONNA DO
WITH THIS THING?
- THAT'S IT!
SOCK IT TO HIM, INUYASHA!
I THINK THE FIRST ONE HIT.
- WHAT, ARE YOU NUTS?
THAT WASN'T EVEN CLOSE.
- BUT THE SWORD'S YOURS NOW.
ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS BELIEVE IN IT--
LIKE I BELIEVE IN YOU.
- YOU ARE NUTS.
THIS SWORD
IS GOOD FOR NOTHING.
ME, I'LL LIVE.
I'M HALF DEMON.
YOU, THOUGH?
YOU AIN'T GOT A CHANCE.
- SO I SHOULD JUST...
GIVE UP HOPE?
- WHAT--WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE NOT CRYING, ARE YOU?
NO CRYING!
- OH, SHOULD I LAUGH?
- NO, YOU SHOULD SHUT UP
AND LET ME PROTECT YOU.
[GASPS]
- HEH. YOU STAY HERE
AND WATCH.
- WAIT A SEC.
I DIDN'T IMAGINE THAT,
DID I?
DID HE JUST SAY
HE'D PROTECT ME?
IN SOME WAYS
HE IS LIKE HIS BROTHER,
BUT IN OTHERS
HE'S TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
- YEAH, YEAH.
ROAR, ROAR,
TO YOU, TOO, BUDDY.
LET'S GET IT OVER WITH.
[HEART BEATING]
HUH?
TETSUSAIGA IS PULSING.
I CAN HEAR IT--
THE SOUND FROM BEFORE.
NO, THIS TIME
IT'S DIFFERENT.
- GET HIM, LORD SESSHOMARU!
BITE HIS LITTLE HEAD OFF!
THAT'S RIGHT!
NIBBLE OF HIS LITTLE--OW!
- WE'LL SEE WHO EATS WHO.
- D'OH!
- YOU CAN DO IT.
I JUST KNOW IT.
- NOW.
IT LOOKS LIKE A BANG.
[CHUCKLES]
IT IS A BANG.
THE OLD MAN
REALLY DID LEAVE
SOMETHING WORTHWHILE.
SO HERE WE ARE,
TWO BROTHERS FIGHTING OVER
FATHER'S SWORD.
BUT COMPARED TO HIM,
YOU AND ME ARE NOTHING.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
WE'RE LIKE A COUPLE OF FLEAS
JUMPING AROUND ON HIS BODY.
HUH. WE'D BE LUCKY
IF HE DIDN'T SQUASH US FLAT.
SO MAYBE I DON'T HAVE
TOO MANY MEMORIES OF HIM,
BUT IT WAS ME
FATHER CHOSE TO HIDE
HIS TOMB IN, AFTER ALL.
I'D RATHER GIVE UP AN EYE
THAN GIVE UP HIS SWORD.
MAYBE I'M NOT SO WORTHLESS
THEN, AM I?
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
DON'T LEAVE ME!
- INUYASHA?
INUYASHA, ARE YOU OK?
[CHUCKLES]
- I TAKE IT BACK.
SO THE SWORD'S NOT
SUCH A PIECE OF JUNK.
- YOU SEE? I WAS RIGHT.
OF COURSE,
IF YOU'D LISTENED EARLIER,
YOU'D NEVER HAVE--
WAIT. OVER THERE. SEE?
I WASN'T RUNNING AWAY.
I WAS GETTING US
A RIDE HOME.
YOU BELIEVE ME, RIGHT?
- OH, SO THEN
YOU DIDN'T RUN AWAY?
- I DIDN'T?
OK, I ADMIT IT.
I RAN AWAY.
BUT YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME,
IF I'D KNOWN
YOU'D MAKE A COMEBACK,
I WOULD NEVER
HAVE LEFT YOU.
I'M ASHAMED OF MYSELF.
I OUGHTA HAVE MORE FAITH.
PLEASE--
PLEASE, FORGIVE ME!
IF ONLY I COULD
MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
- MYOGA...
- OH, WELL.
SUCH IS A FLEA'S
LOT IN LIFE.
- SO, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- ACTUALLY,
I FEEL PRETTY OK.
EVERYTHING'S
BACK TO NORMAL.
AND AT LEAST NOW I KNOW
THAT THE OLD MAN
CAN REST IN PEACE.
- BUT HOW IS IT
THAT YE, CHILD,
WERE ABLE TO PULL
THE TETSUSAIGA?
I MUST SAY,
YE CONTINUE TO SURPRISE ME.
- HMM.
- MY THEORY
IS THAT IT IS BECAUSE
KAGOME IS MORTAL.
DON'T FORGET,
TETSUSAIGA WAS FORGED BY
LORD INUYASHA'S FATHER
AS A WAY TO PROTECT
HIS MORTAL MOTHER.
IT WAS HIS FEELINGS
TOWARDS MORTALS
THAT ALLOWED LORD INUYASHA
TO WIELD IT EFFECTIVELY.
- NO, YOU SHOULD SHUT UP
AND LET ME PROTECT YOU.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S WHEN THE SWORD REACTED.
- TETSUSAIGA IS PULSING.
- FOR SOMEONE LIKE SESSHOMARU
WHO COULD ONLY HATE HUMANS,
WIELDING TETSUSAIGA
WAS IMPOSSIBLE.
- 'TIS A STRANGE STORY, AYE.
TO INUYASHA,
HIS HALF-HUMAN HERITAGE
HAS BEEN A CURSE.
HIS FEELINGS FOR HIS MOTHER
HAVE BEEN TINGED WITH SHAME.
AND YET, THOSE SAME FEELINGS
ARE WHAT MAKE HIM DIFFERENT.
THAT IS WHY HIS FATHER CHOSE HIM
FOR HIS RESTING PLACE.
PERHAPS THE ONE
WHO MOST RESEMBLES
THE FATHER
IS NOT SESSHOMARU,
BUT INUYASHA.
- HMM.
[CLANG]
I SPOKE TOO SOON.
NOW IT'S BACK
TO BEING A PIECE OF JUNK.
- INUYASHA?
- WHAT?
- DO YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU?
YOU KNOW,
HOW TO USE TETSUSAIGA?
- AND SINCE WHEN
ARE YOU AN EXPERT?
- WELL, DO YOU PROMISE
YOU'LL PROTECT ME WITH IT
FOREVER AND EVER?
- HUH?
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU BABBLING ABOUT?
YOUR BRAIN'S BROKEN
OR SOMETHING.
- BUT YOU SAID
I SHOULD LET YOU PROTECT ME!
- I DIDN'T MEAN IT
LIKE THAT!
IF YOU'LL SHUT UP FOR A MINUTE,
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT A SWORD LIKE THIS
SHOULD REALLY
BE USED FOR.
STUFF LIKE
COLLECTING JEWEL SHARDS
AND MAKING ME MORE POWERFUL.
I SURE AS HECK
AIN'T WASTING IT
ON BABY-SITTING A HELPLESS
LITTLE HUMAN LIKE YOU.
- HMPH!
- I DON'T GET IT.
SIT, BOY.
IT'S MY FAULT FOR THINKING
I COULD TEACH AN OLD DOG
A NEW TRICK.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "TRICK"?
WAIT! WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
COME BACK HERE!
YOU SAID YOU'D TELL ME
HOW TO USE THE SWORD!
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- SESSHOMARU'S DOWN,
BUT HE'S NOT OUT.
PLUS, HIS LEFT ARM
IS STILL INSIDE
THEIR FATHER'S TOMB.
NOW THAT INUYASHA
HAS TETSUSAIGA,
THE SEARCH FOR MORE
JEWEL SHARDS CONTINUES.
THEY'LL BE A TOWN,
SOME KIDNAPPED GIRLS,
AND A YOUNG SAMURAI
TRYING TO SAVE THE PRINCESS.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!