[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
- IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
UGH!
- OH, INUYASHA.
[ROARING]
- UGH!
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
AAH!
[GROANING]
- INUYASHA!
[LAUGHTER]
- NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
YOUR MEASURES ARE ALL IN VAIN.
SURRENDER AND FIND A NEW HOME
INSIDE MY DEMON'S BELLY.
[GROANING]
- SO WHAT IF I CAN'T USE
THE TETSUSAIGA.
I ONLY NEED ONE ARM TO TAKE OUT
THAT REPULSIVE DEMON!
- HOLD YOUR TONGUE!
[GROWLING AND ROARING]
- BLADES OF BLOOD!
[GROWLING]
- HUH!
[CHUCKLES]
HMMPH!
DON'T BE SO SURE
OF YOURSELF.
[GROANING]
- KAGOME!
WHY, YOU--
- DO NOT FORGET, INUYASHA.
I HOLD KAGOME'S
VERY LIFE IN MY HAND.
[SIGHS]
[GROWLING]
[ROARS]
- DAMN!
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
ARE YOU IN PAIN, KAGOME?
- YEAH, BUT I'M FINE, SANGO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
[MOANS]
- COME ON, MIROKU.
WE HAVE TO HELP INUYASHA.
KAGOME WON'T BE ABLE
TO LAST FOR VERY LONG.
- HOLD ON.
I FIGURE TSUBAKI INTENDS
TO KILL KAGOME
WHETHER INUYASHA WINS
OR LOSES THIS BATTLE.
- YOU MEAN--
- RIGHT.
OUR ONLY HOPE IS TO FIND A WAY
TO BREAK TSUBAKI'S CURSE.
EITHER WE DESTROY TSUBAKI
OR WE KILL SHIKIGAMI,
HER DEMON PUPPET.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
REMEMBER JUST BEFORE
KAGOME FELL ILL,
SHE SAID SHE'D BEEN
BITTEN AT THE WELL.
- EXACTLY. IT WAS MORE THAN
LIKELY THAT DEMON SERPENT.
I'M ALMOST SURE OF IT.
BACK ME UP, SANGO!
- YOU CAN COUNT ON IT!
[PANTING]
[GROWLING]
- AAH! AAH!
- HIRAIKOTSU!
[GROWLING]
[PANTING]
- HYAH!
[CHUCKLES]
- EXORCISM SUTRAS.
THEY'RE USELESS ON ME!
[ROARS]
- OHH!
- FOOL!
MY CURSE CANNOT BE BROKEN!
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
OH, NO!
[ROARS]
- MIROKU!
- YOU SEEM TO ENJOY PAIN.
JUST REMEMBER,
THE LONGER YOU RESIST ME,
THE LONGER HER SUFFERING
WILL BE PROLONGED.
[GROANING]
IT WOULD BE SO EASY TO END.
SHALL I SEND KAGOME TO HER
DEMISE THIS VERY INSTANT?
- AAH!
- KAGOME!
KAGOME,
YOU'VE GOT TO BE STRONG!
KAGOME! SAY SOMETHING!
- I HEAR YOU, SANGO.
I'LL WAKE UP IN A MINUTE.
WAIT FOR ME.
[ALARM RINGING]
WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
IT'S SO NOISY.
- KAGOME? KAGOME!
KAGOME!
- SOMEONE'S CALLING ME.
WHO IS IT?
I CAN'T REMEMBER.
- KAGOME, WAKE UP
OR YOU'LL BE LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- HUH?
[ALARM STOPS]
YOU CAN'T STAY IN BED
FOREVER, YOUNG LADY.
[GASPS]
- WHAT HAPPENED TO SANGO?
AND INUYASHA?
AND MIROKU?
HOW THE HECK DID I END UP
BACK IN THIS WORLD?
- SOUNDS LIKE QUITE THE DREAM.
HURRY AND COME DOWNSTAIRS.
BREAKFAST WILL
BE READY FOR YOU.
- HUH?
- OH, GOOD MORNING, KAGOME.
- HONESTLY, GIRL.
CAN'T YOU AT LEAST
SAY "GOOD MORNING"?
- MORNING.
HANG ON.
CAN YOU TELL ME WHEN EXACTLY
I CAME BACK HERE?
- BACK WHERE?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DID YOU GO SOMEWHERE?
- YOU KNOW.
WHERE I'M ALWAYS GOING.
THE OTHER DIMENSION?
500 YEARS IN THE PAST.
REMEMBER?
WHEN I GO DOWN THAT
OLD, HIDDEN WELL,
I END UP BACK IN THE FEUDAL ERA
WHERE THERE ARE TONS OF DEMONS.
- OH! YOU WENT
INTO THAT WELL?
- DUH! ONLY ABOUT
100 TIMES ALREADY.
INUYASHA CAME HERE, TOO,
REMEMBER?
- INUYASHA?
- WHAT ON EARTH IS THAT?
- YOU MEAN, YOU'VE
FORGOTTEN ABOUT HIM?
GRAMPS, ARE YOU FEELING OK?
YOU KNOW, HE'S THE GUY
WITH THE DOG EARS.
- HMM.
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
- NO KIDDING!
MAYBE YOU SHOULD STAY HOME
FROM SCHOOL TODAY, SIS.
- SHE'S STILL HALF ASLEEP.
- OH, DEAR.
[ALL SIGH]
NO WAY.
- KAGOME, YOU'LL BE
LATE FOR SCHOOL!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
HAS THIS WHOLE THING
BEEN JUST A DREAM?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU, KAGOME?
- YOU SEEM KIND OF DOWN.
- WELL...
- YOU'VE GOT A PROBLEM?
- LIKE...BOYFRIEND TROUBLE?
- BOYFRIEND?
THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU GUYS ALL REMEMBER
MY BOYFRIEND, DON'T YOU?
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
SURE WE DO.
- YES! IT WASN'T
A DREAM AFTER ALL!
- IT'S HOJO!
HE'S IN GROUP "B."
[LAUGHTER]
[SIGHS WITH FRUSTRATION]
- DUH! REMEMBER?
ATTITUDE MAN?
YOU KNOW, MR. POSSESSIVE?
- WHO'S THAT?
YOU WERE TWO-TIMING ON HOJO?
- NO! NO! NO!
- WOW, YOU SURE GO FOR IT!
[SIGHS]
HUH?
- I DON'T GET IT.
SUDDENLY I'VE BEEN THRUST
BACK INTO MY OLD LIFE.
- HIGURASHI.
- YES?
- READ THE NEXT PART.
- OK.
UH...
- WHAT'S THE MATTER NOW?
- I DON'T GET IT.
- ENTRANCE EXAMS
ARE COMING UP SOON.
YOU BETTER START
PAYING ATTENTION.
[SIGHS]
- ENTRANCE EXAMS.
YEAH, I'M SUPPOSED
TO STUDY FOR EXAMS.
THAT'S MY REAL LIFE.
THAT WAS HOW I WANTED
MY LIFE TO BE.
BUT THEN...
- KAGOME!
- HUH?
- HEY. YOU.
- HERE.
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
THIS WILL CHEER YOU UP
AND WORK WONDERS
ON THE ACUPRESSURE POINTS
OF YOUR SOLES.
ONE STEP AND YOU'LL BE SOLD.
[CHUCKLES]
- SOMETHING'S WRONG.
I JUST KNOW THIS ISN'T
THE WAY IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE.
- I WANT TO HAVE LOTS OF KIDS.
- YOU'RE SUCH A JOKER.
- GRANDMA, BUY ME
A SACRED JEWEL KEY HOLDER.
- SURE.
- THE SACRED JEWEL, YOU SAY.
- SACRED JEWEL?
- I BET YOU'VE NEVER HEARD
THE ORIGIN OF THE JEWEL.
MY OWN GRANDFATHER...
- HA HA!
LET'S GO, GRANDMA.
- ALL RIGHT.
- ...LONG AGO,
DEEP IN THE MOUNTAINS
WHERE MANY FEAR TO TREAD...
[KAGOME GROANING]
HELLO?
WHERE'D EVERYBODY GO?
[MOANS]
[CAT MEOWING]
- HUH?
BUYO, I THINK THERE MIGHT BE
SOMETHING WRONG WITH ME.
[CAT GRUMBLES]
THERE ARE JUST SO MANY THINGS
RACING AROUND INSIDE MY HEAD.
IT FEELS LIKE I WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE DOING SOMETHING RIGHT NOW,
BUT I CAN'T THINK
OF WHAT IT WAS.
[CAT GRUMBLES]
THINGS I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD
REMEMBER ARE SLOWLY FADING AWAY.
[BELL DINGING]
I HAVE THIS FEELING THAT
WHAT I'M DOING NOW IS WRONG.
BUT WHAT IS IT THAT
I'M SUPPOSED TO DO?
I'M GETTING USED TO THIS PAIN
I SOMETIMES GET IN MY NECK.
AND NOW I HARDLY
EVEN WORRY ABOUT IT.
WHO AM I?
AND WHY AM I HERE?
WHAT AM I DOING?
HOW COME I FEEL SO ANXIOUS
AND SO UNCERTAIN?
[GASPS]
- WHAT'S WRONG, KAGOME?
- I'M SORRY.
I GOT TO GO, HOJO!
- KAGOME?
ALL RIGHT, NEXT UP.
OH, YOU'VE FINALLY ARRIVED.
- UH, I, UH...
- WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY?
- HUH?
- ISN'T THAT WHY YOU'VE COME?
- MM-HMM.
- AIM FOR THAT TARGET.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YOUR LINE IS GOOD.
- HIT THE MARK.
- YOU NEED MORE PRACTICE.
YOUR CONCENTRATION IS LACKING.
- EXCUSE ME.
WHO EXACTLY--
- WHO ARE YOU?
- UH!
- ME? I'M, UH...
- ARE YOU...
ARE YOU ME?
WATCH YOURSELF, OR YOU'LL END UP
KILLING INUYASHA AGAIN.
- INUYASHA?
[GROANS]
- KAGOME!
[MOANING]
COME ON.
HANG IN THERE, KAGOME.
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
- IN...INUYASHA!
[MOANING]
WAIT!
I HAVE TO GET UP
FROM THIS WORLD!
- HMMPH!
- WAIT, I SAID!
NO! PLEASE, STOP!
WAIT, I SAID!
COME BACK HERE!
PLEASE, STOP!
- TELL ME WHO YOU ARE.
- THAT ISN'T IMPORTANT NOW!
- THIS IS A WORLD
OF YOUR OWN MAKING.
YOU HAVE DECIDED
WHO YOU ARE.
NOW, ANSWER ME!
TELL ME WHO YOU ARE!
[MOANS]
- KAGOME!
- INUYASHA!
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLS]
- AAH!
UGH!
[GROWLING]
- INUYASHA!
[ROARING]
- WHAT?
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
WENCH! WHY ARE YOU
STILL ABLE TO MOVE?
- WELL, I CAN.
MAYBE YOU'RE NOT
CONCENTRATING HARD ENOUGH.
- HUH! WELL, YOU'VE CERTAINLY
MANAGED TO ENDURE MY SPELL.
SO IT WOULD SEEM THAT
YOU TRULY ARE KIKYO'S
REINCARNATION AFTER ALL.
ALTHOUGH...IF YOU ACTUALLY
WERE THE REAL KIKYO,
THAT ARROW MOST CERTAINLY
WOULDN'T HAVE MISSED ME,
MEANING YOU'RE
AN IMITATION KIKYO.
- YOU'LL REGRET THAT.
- TELL ME WHO YOU ARE.
- I AM KAGOME!
I'M NOT ANYONE ELSE!
- HMM.
- HMMPH!
- YOU ARE FOOLISH,
RUSHING TO YOUR DEATH.
[HISSES]
[GROANING AND CHOKING]
- KAGOME!
- OHH!
[GROANING]
[ROARING]
- AAH!
- KAGOME!
[MOANING]
- SHE WON'T LAST MUCH LONGER.
[GRUNTING]
- KAGOME...JUST BE
STRONG A BIT LONGER.
- YEAH, SURE.
I CAN HANG ON A WHILE.
- KAGOME.
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU TWO!
[GROWLING]
- I'LL NEVER LET YOU KILL HER!
YOU BETTER STAY
OUT OF MY WAY!
IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
HYAH!
[GAGGING]
THIS IS THE END, TSUBAKI!
[GASPING]
- WELL DONE, INUYASHA!
[GRUNTS]
ONE DOWN.
- SORRY ABOUT YOUR
SERPENT, TSUBAKI.
- HA HA HA!
YOU'RE NAIVE.
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
THE CURSE HAS BEEN BROKEN?
- WHAT?
- THE SPELL STILL
HOLDS, YOU FOOL.
- HUH?
[GROANING]
- SHE'S NOT RECOVERING,
EVEN THOUGH SHIKIGAMI
WAS DESTROYED.
- KAGOME WILL DIE.
OH, YES.
AND THE REST OF YOU.
- HUH?
[DEMONS ROARING]
UGH!
AHH!
HUH?
- SHE HAD MORE
DEMONS INSIDE HER!
- DAMN THAT WITCH TO HELL!
[GRUNTING]
- KIRARA, STAY HERE
AND PROTECT KAGOME.
HIRAIKOTSU!
- UGH! HYAH!
[GRASS RUSTLING]
- HUH?
- HMM.
- SHIKIGAMI!
IT COULDN'T BE!
- UGH! DAMN IT!
THESE DEMONS WERE
JUST A DIVERSION!
- CORRECT, BUT NOW
IT'S FAR TOO LATE!
SHIKIGAMI!
BITE OFF THAT WOMAN'S HEAD
AND GET THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS FROM HER!
- KAGOME!
DAMN IT! I WON'T MAKE IT
TO HER IN TIME!
[GROANING]
- NOT THIS TIME, SCALY!
YOU BIT ME BY THE WELL.
YOU WON'T GET ME AGAIN!
NO CHANCE!
THIS TIME...
VICTORY IS MINE!
- OH, NO!
AAH!
[GASPING]
- SHE THREW THE SERPENT AT HER!
- SHE SENT MY CURSE
BACK TO ME,
JUST AS KIKYO DID!
JUST LIKE THAT LAST TIME!
[HISSING]
[GASP]
[SCREAMING]
WHY MUST I BE DONE IN
BY THAT YOUNG WENCH?
[SIGHING]
[GASP]
THE JEWEL IS BEGINNING
TO PURIFY!
[SHATTERING]
- THE SHARDS HAVE COME OUT!
- IT CAN'T BE!
[GRUNTING]
WHY, YOU--
- SHE'S GETTING AWAY!
- NOT FROM ME!
I'M NOT FINISHED WITH YOU YET!
HA!
- NO! NO!
- DAMN! SHE GOT AWAY.
KAGOME!
[GROANING]
- INU...YASHA.
- SO, IS THAT IT?
YOU INTEND TO LET HER LEAVE
WITH YOUR SACRED JEWEL?
- OF COURSE NOT.
I'LL SOON GET IT BACK.
BESIDES...
- BESIDES WHAT?
- I MUST GIVE THE DARK
PRIESTESS THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SEEK HER REVENGE.
[SCOFFS]
- HOW VERY KIND AND
CONSIDERATE OF YOU.
- HMM.
- MY POWERS HAVE WANED,
AND THANKS TO THOSE FOOLS,
MY DEMONS HAVE ALL PERISHED.
I WAS SO CLOSE TO VICTORY.
AT LEAST I'LL BE ABLE
TO INCREASE MY POWERS IMMENSELY
WITH A SACRED JEWEL THIS LARGE.
I'LL DEFEAT YOU NEXT TIME.
I'LL GET REVENGE
FOR THIS HUMILIATION,
INUYASHA AND KAGOME!
- KAGOME MUST BE SO TIRED.
- CAN'T BLAME HER.
SHE WAS UNDER A SPELL
FOR SO LONG.
- INUYASHA! KAGOME!
OVER HERE!
HA HA HA HA!
- I'M SORRY, KAGOME.
THIS ONLY HAPPENED,
BECAUSE YOU'RE WITH ME.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- HUH?
- I'M WITH YOU BY CHOICE.
- KAGOME.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- DOES TSUBAKI,
THE DARK PRIESTESS,
STILL HAVE THE SACRED JEWEL?
THAT SPELLS TROUBLE.
WAIT--A RED PRIESTESS
AND A WHITE PRIESTESS?
WHO ARE THEY?
TSUBAKI'S HELPERS?
THEY LOOK SO IMPORTANT.
WHAT?
I'M NOT TRICKING KAGOME
AND MIROKU AND THE OTHERS.
THAT'S A LIE!
NEXT TIME, "THE RED
AND WHITE PRIESTESSES."
I'D BETTER LIVE UP
TO MY REPUTATION.