- I'M KAGOME HIGURASHI,
A NINTH-GRADER.
MY FAMILY AND I ARE CARETAKERS
OF A VERY OLD HISTORIC SHRINE,
AND UP UNTIL RECENTLY,
I LED A PRETTY NORMAL LIFE.
BUT ON MY 15th BIRTHDAY, I WAS
DRAGGED INTO THE FEUDAL ERA
BY A DEMON WHO SUDDENLY EMERGED
FROM THE OLD SHRINE WELL.
THERE, COUNTLESS DEMONS WISHING
TO INCREASE THEIR POWER
SEARCHED FOR THE SACRED
SHIKON JEWEL.
THIS IS WHERE I MET
A HALF-DEMON NAMED INUYASHA.
INUYASHA WANTS THE SACRED JEWEL
TO BECOME A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
SINCE WE MET,
WE'VE TRAVELED TOGETHER
IN SEARCH OF SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
THAT ARE SCATTERED
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY.
WE'VE FOUGHT MANY DEMONS
ON OUR JOURNEY,
BUT WE'VE ALSO MADE FRIENDS
ALONG THE WAY...
LIKE SHIPPO, A VERY
CUTE FOX DEMON CHILD.
HE ALWAYS TRIES SO HARD, AND HE
HELPS US WITH HIS FOX MAGIC.
AND THE MONK, MIROKU.
THE WIND TUNNEL ON HIS PALM,
INFLICTED BY NARAKU'S CURSE,
HAS THE POWER TO SUCK UP
ANYTHING IN ITS PATH.
HE'S FAIRLY DEPENDABLE,
AT LEAST MOST OF THE TIME.
SANGO IS THE LAST SURVIVOR
OF A TRIBE OF DEMON SLAYERS.
HER MISSION IS TO DESTROY NARAKU
TO AVENGE HER PEOPLE.
NARAKU IS THE MOST
DESPICABLE DEMON OF ALL.
HE RESORTS TO DIRTY TRICKS
AND DEVIOUS TRAPS
TO BRING DOWN HIS ENEMIES
WITHOUT NEEDING TO SULLY
HIS OWN HANDS.
HE IS STEADILY ACCUMULATING
SHARDS OF THE JEWEL,
GROWING MORE AND MORE
POWERFUL ALL THE WHILE.
WE'LL POOL OUR STRENGTH AND
SOMEDAY FIND NARAKU'S CASTLE.
TOGETHER, WE'LL BRING HIM DOWN.
OUR JOURNEY IS FAR FROM OVER.
[PANTING]
- I'M SO SORRY.
I WAS OVERCOME BY PAIN.
- DON'T MENTION IT.
IT'S ALL PART OF A MONK'S DUTY.
- NOT AGAIN.
- LOOKS LIKE IT.
- YEP. HE'S AT IT AGAIN.
- HOW ARE YOU NOW?
- I FEEL BETTER ALREADY,
THANKS TO YOUR GENTLE
TOUCH AND KINDNESS.
- DON'T OVEREXERT YOURSELF.
- NO. I'M QUITE FINE NOW.
- THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
VERY WELL.
BY THE WAY--
- YES?
- WOULD YOU BE INTERESTED
IN BEARING MY CHILD?
- NOT THAT AGAIN.
- SURE LOOKS LIKE IT.
- YEP.
HE'S AT IT AGAIN.
[SIGHS]
- I'LL BE OFF.
- TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
- MIROKU, WHY DO YOU
ALWAYS ACT LIKE THAT
WHEN YOU COME ACROSS
A PRETTY LADY?
- WHAT?
YOU CAN'T EXPECT ME TO IGNORE
A FEMALE IN DISTRESS, CAN YOU?
[SCOFFS]
LET'S CARRY ON, SHALL WE?
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO KEPT US
WAITING, REMEMBER?
- THANK YOU.
COME AGAIN.
- AH!
HOW ABOUT A SHORT BREAK?
- EXCELLENT IDEA.
[GASPS]
- HUH?
- IS SOMETHING
THE MATTER, MIROKU?
- MY TRAVEL FUNDS!
MY MONEY!
IT'S DISAPPEARED!
I'M SURE I HAD IT
THIS MORNING.
- THAT WOMAN AT THE ROADSIDE
MUST HAVE BEEN A PICKPOCKET.
- NO WONDER
SHE DIDN'T GO BERSERK
WHEN YOU STARTED GIVING HER
REAR A GOOD MASSAGE.
- OH, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
- MOVE ALONG, LECHER.
[SIGHS]
- HUH?
MIROKU'S GONE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
- HE WAS LAGGING BEHIND
UP UNTIL A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
- MAYBE HE'S A LITTLE DEPRESSED
ABOUT BEING ROBBED.
- I'LL GO AND CHECK.
[SIGHS]
- WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
- NOTHING.
I WAS JUST THINKING.
- OH, I SEE.
- WE'RE WORRIED SICK AND DON'T
HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT WE SHOULD DO.
- WELL, THERE'S NO NEED
TO WORRY ANY LONGER.
- MIND EXPLAINING WHAT
YOU'RE DOING THERE, MONK?
- AAH! HI.
NOTHING AS OF YET.
- SO YOU SAY THE MEN WHO
WENT INTO THE MOUNTAIN
HAVEN'T RETURNED?
- WE'RE SURE THEY'VE BEEN
CAPTURED BY A DEMON.
PLEASE HELP US.
- HE NEVER MISSES
A CHANCE TO PLAY THE HERO.
- THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH HELPING THEM.
- PLEASE ASSIST US.
- WE NEED YOUR HELP.
- I AM BEGGING YOU TO PLEASE
HELP ME FIND MY HUSBAND.
- YOU MEAN, YOU'RE
MARRIED AS WELL?
- YES.
- OH.
- HMM?
- IT MUST BE VERY LONELY
WITHOUT YOUR HUSBAND.
- YES, AND THAT'S WHY
WE NEED YOUR ASSISTANCE.
- VERY WELL.
THEN WE SHALL GO FREE YOUR
HUSBANDS FROM THE DEMON.
- THANK YOU.
WE'RE EVER SO GRATEFUL.
- DID YOU GET
ALL THAT, INUYASHA?
- YEAH, I'LL HELP,
SEEING AS HOW I'M THE ONE
WHO WILL HAVE TO DO
ALL THE FIGHTING.
- EXACTLY.
- HMM.
[SIGHS]
- LET'S BE OFF, THEN, SHALL WE?
- PLEASE BE VERY CAREFUL,
MY FRIENDS.
ACCORDING TO RUMORS,
THE DEMON IS IN THE FORM
OF A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
- IT WOULD BE BEST FOR ALL
IF I WENT ALONE.
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
- WHY DID MIROKU
WANT TO GO BY HIMSELF?
- HE PROBABLY WANTS SOME TIME
ALONE WITH THE BEAUTIFUL DEMON.
- THAT GUY NEVER LEARNS,
DOES HE?
[FOOTSTEPS]
HUH?
- SANGO, ARE YOU
GOING AFTER HIM?
- OF COURSE.
IF THAT WOMANIZING MONK
GOES ALONE,
HE'LL GET BEWITCHED JUST
LIKE ALL THE OTHERS HAVE.
COME ON, KIRARA.
- SAY, INUYASHA?
- HMM?
- IS IT JUST ME,
OR DO YOU GET THE FEELING
THAT MAYBE SANGO HAS
THE HOTS FOR MIROKU?
- HUH?
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS?
- DON'T TELL ME YOU HAVEN'T
NOTICED ANYTHING.
- HMM?
- I NOTICED IT A LONG TIME AGO.
- BUT I--
- YOU'RE EVEN DENSER
THAN I THOUGHT.
- THEN HOW COME SANGO
ALWAYS GETS MAD
WHENEVER MIROKU TRIES
TO STROKE HER BUTT?
- BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO SET UP
THE RIGHT ATMOSPHERE FOR WOMEN.
- ATMOSPHERE AS IN CLOUDS
AND STUFF?
- HUH?
UH...LOOK,
SANGO LIKES MIROKU.
TRUST ME.
I KNOW THESE THINGS.
- I DON'T KNOW.
[SIGHS]
- DO YOU MIND?
- WHAT ARE YOU SIGHING FOR?
- NOTHING.
- YOU DO REALIZE WE'RE
ON OUR WAY TO DESTROY
A DEMON, DON'T YOU?
- I KNOW.
- ACCORDING TO THE VILLAGERS,
A LONG TIME AGO,
DEFEATED SOLDIERS FLED
DEEP INTO THIS MOUNTAIN.
AND THERE WAS
A PRINCESS AMONG THEM,
BUT ALL THE MEN
WHO PROTECTED HER DIED.
THEY SAY THAT, IN THE END,
THE PRINCESS HERSELF DIED
AS WELL.
- OH? AND HER BITTERNESS
TURNED HER INTO A DEMON?
- I SUPPOSE SO.
- HMM.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT'S
THE FATE THAT WOMEN SEEM
TO BE BURDENED WITH.
- HUH?
- I'VE EXPERIENCED
THE WHOLE GAMUT.
WOMEN ARE PERSISTENT, PRONE TO
JEALOUSY AND BURSTS OF ANGER,
NOT TO MENTION HATRED.
- PRETTY KNOWLEDGEABLE
FOR SOMEONE WHO'S A MONK.
- EVEN I CAN'T IMAGINE WHAT KIND
OF TERRIBLE DEMON IS CREATED
BY THE BITTERNESS OF A PRINCESS
WHO DIES A SAD AND LONELY DEATH.
I JUST HAD TO SEE IT
WITH MY OWN EYES.
- I UNDERSTAND, BUT WHY
INSIST ON GOING ALONE?
- I HAVE REASONS.
- HUH?
- DO YOU SEE THAT
OVER THERE, SANGO?
IT'S THE ENTRANCE
TO THE DEMON'S LAIR--
THE BARRIER, IF YOU WILL.
IT SEEMS EASY ENOUGH TO ENTER,
BUT IT'S PROBABLY
DIFFICULT TO COME OUT.
HERE. PUT THIS ON, SANGO.
IT MAY PROVE HELPFUL ONCE
WE'RE ON THE OTHER SIDE.
- RIGHT.
- OK. LET'S GET GOING.
- I THOUGHT HE SAID IT WAS
GONNA BE EASY TO ENTER.
HE MUST HAVE BEEN KIDDING.
IT'S EXTREMELY RESISTANT.
MIROKU, WAIT UP FOR ME.
MIROKU!
- SANGO!
WHERE ARE YOU, SANGO?
MUST HAVE LOST HER ON THE WAY.
HMM?
IS THAT A MANSION?
- WHO GOES?
- HMM?
- WHY ARE YOU HERE
SO DEEP IN THIS MOUNTAIN?
- IS THIS GIRL THE DEMON?
- I KNOW NOT WHY YOU COME,
BUT PLEASE FOLLOW ME
TO THE MANSION.
- MIROKU, WHERE ARE YOU?
MIROKU?
DEMONS?
HUMANS!
AND THEY'RE ALL OLD MEN.
EXCUSE ME, OLD MAN.
I SAID EXCUSE ME, OLD MAN.
- YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
I AIN'T AN OLD MAN.
- SURE YOU ARE.
YOU'RE ALL OLD.
- I SAID I AIN'T AN OLD MAN.
- YEAH.
I AIN'T OLD EITHER.
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING OLD?
I AIN'T OLD.
[SIGHS]
- NO, MA'AM,
I AIN'T AN OLD MAN.
- NONE OF YOU ARE OLD MEN?
- MIROKU'S THE REAL
PROBLEM HERE.
I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE
HOW HE FEELS ABOUT SANGO.
- HE AIN'T FUSSY.
HE SEEMS TO LIKE ALL WOMEN.
- BUT MAYBE HE FEELS STRONGER
ABOUT SANGO, THOUGH.
- COULD BE.
HE GOES AFTER HER BUTT ENOUGH.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
- OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
THAT ISN'T WHAT I MEANT.
- OK, I'M READY
FOR A CHANGE OF TOPIC.
- HANG ON.
YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT
ALL OF YOU ARE THE MEN
WHO DISAPPEARED
FROM THE VILLAGE?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- YEAH, IT WAS LIKE
A DREAM, REALLY.
- I FOUND MYSELF LOST
AND IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
THEN SUDDENLY THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
PRINCESS APPEARED BEFORE ME
DEEP IN THE MOUNTAINS.
SHE BROUGHT ME
TO A MAGNIFICENT VILLA,
AND I SPENT SUCH A GRAND TIME.
- A GRAND TIME, YOU SAY?
- YES.
IT WAS MOST ENJOYABLE.
- AYE.
ENJOYABLE AND GRAND.
- THE NEXT THING WE KNEW, WE ALL
FOUND OURSELVES LIKE THIS.
- THE DEMON DRAINED
THE LIFE SPIRIT,
THE YOUTH OUT OF THESE MEN.
- THEN YOU MUST
HAVE SURVIVED THE WAR.
DID YOU, PRINCESS?
- AYE.
UNFORTUNATELY ALL OF MY VASSALS
PERISHED IN MY DEFENSE.
I AM ALL ALONE
AND SO VERY LONELY.
- VERY TRAGIC INDEED.
- MONK?
- HMM?
- IT IS MY FATE TO REMAIN HERE.
WOULD YOU DO ME THE KINDNESS
OF SPENDING THE NIGHT WITH ME?
- IS THAT YOUR HONEST DESIRE?
- YES, IT IS.
LOOK AT ME.
LOOK DEEP INTO MY EYES.
- AND WHEN THE PRINCESS
GAZED AT YOU
WITH THOSE BEAUTIFUL
EYES OF HERS--
- I FELL INTO A DAZE,
AND SUDDENLY NOTHING ELSE
MATTERED ANYMORE
EXCEPT THE PRINCESS.
- KIRARA, YOU STAY HERE
WITH THE MEN.
I'VE GOT TO HURRY.
IF I KNOW THAT WOMANIZING MONK,
HE'LL FALL RIGHT INTO HER TRAP.
- PRINCESS.
- MONK.
- BE STRONG, MIROKU.
JUST STAY ALIVE
UNTIL I GET THERE.
I'LL SAVE YOU.
AAH!
WHY THAT--
WAKE UP, YOU LECHER!
- A WOMAN'S VOICE.
AAH!
- PRINCESS.
[GROWLING]
- WHERE ARE YOU, WENCH?
I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU
TO INTERFERE!
- SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHERE I AM.
SHE CAN'T SEE ME.
ALL RIGHT.
- WAIT, SANGO!
- MIROKU, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE UNDER HER SPELL.
- SHE WON'T BE ABLE TO FIND YOU
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP QUIET.
- I UNDERSTAND.
THE BEADS MIROKU LENT ME MUST
MAKE ME INVISIBLE TO THE DEMON.
BUT THEN, WHY ISN'T
HE DESTROYING HER?
- THE TRUE FORM OF THE DEMON
IS A FEMALE COYOTE.
- I SHALL SUCK
THE LIFE FORCE FROM YOU!
[GRUNTING]
- YOU OK?
- KEEP YOUR DISTANCE.
I WAS HOPING TO TAKE
CARE OF THIS WITHOUT
THE NEED FOR A BATTLE.
[ROARING]
PRINCESS, YOU'LL HAVE TO ENDURE
SOME PAIN, I'M AFRAID!
AAH!
- DID HE SAY PRINCESS?
- BE STRONG!
[ROARING]
- HUH?
[SCREAMING]
- THERE'S A PRINCESS
INSIDE THE DEMON.
[ROARING]
- PRINCESS!
AAH!
PRINCESS!
- CURSE YOU, MONK!
I SHALL SHOW NO MERCY NOW!
- PRINCESS!
- RETURN THE PRINCESS TO ME!
[GRUNTING]
- SANGO!
- RIGHT.
[SHOUTS]
- AAH!
ARRGH!
WHY, YOU!
WHERE ARE YOU?
[ROARING]
THERE YOU ARE!
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
MY POWER!
THE DEMON POWER
I ACCUMULATED!
[SCREAMING]
- HEY, MIROKU, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHAT HAPPENED.
HUH?
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME FOR BEING
SO ROUGH, PRINCESS.
- YOU SAVED ME.
- YOU WERE ISOLATED FOR SO LONG.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN VERY LONELY.
- YES.
I WAS SO WEAK-HEARTED
AND COWARDLY
THAT I FELL VICTIM
TO AN AWFUL DEMON.
- IT'S ALL OVER NOW.
I'LL TAKE YOU TO THE VILLAGE.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
- SHE DISAPPEARED.
- YES.
THAT WAS HER SOUL.
SHE DIED A LONELY DEATH.
IT WASN'T BITTERNESS.
IT WAS LONELINESS THAT KEPT HER
FROM FINDING PEACE IN DEATH.
THE DEMON COYOTE STOLE
THE PRINCESS' BODY AND SOUL,
THEN IMPERSONATED HER
TO LURE MEN IN,
BUT THEN SUCKED OUT
THEIR YOUTH TO GAIN POWER.
I HAVE BURIED THE PRINCESS'
ASHES HERE IN THIS HUMBLE GRAVE.
IF YOU ALL OFFER UP
YOUR PRAYERS,
I AM SURE THAT SHE WILL
WATCH OVER THE VILLAGE.
- WE THANK YOU VERY MUCH, MONK.
WE'RE SO GRATEFUL YOU
BROUGHT OUR MEN BACK TO US.
- IT SEEMS NO MORE
THAN A PLEASANT DREAM NOW.
- I'LL SAY.
- HEY, CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- YES.
- DID ANYTHING HAPPEN
ON THE MOUNTAIN?
SANGO SEEMS AWFULLY DEPRESSED
SINCE YOU TWO GOT BACK.
- UH, NO.
I CAN'T IMAGINE WHAT
MIGHT BE BOTHERING HER.
[SIGHS]
- SILLY ME.
HOW COULD I BE SO FOOLISH?
- SANGO?
- HUH?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE
NEVER FOLLOWED YOU
INTO THE MOUNTAINS
LIKE THAT, MIROKU.
- NOW, DON'T BE FOOLISH.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO DESTROYED
THE DEMON, AREN'T YOU?
- THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
YOU HELPED ME.
- NO, NO.
I RELIED ON YOUR HELP,
BECAUSE I HAD TRUST
IN YOUR STRENGTH, SANGO.
- HUH?
- YOU'RE IMAGINING THINGS.
SANGO WOULDN'T FALL IN LOVE
WITH THAT PERVERT.
- NOW, THAT'S ATMOSPHERE.
- OK.
I'M READY FOR AN EXPLANATION.
- SANGO, YOU CAME WITH ME,
BECAUSE YOU WERE CONCERNED
ABOUT MY SAFETY.
IS THAT CORRECT?
- WELL, SURE THAT'S WHY I CAME.
YES, OF COURSE I WAS
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY REASONABLE
WHEN YOU'RE AROUND WOMEN,
YOU KNOW.
I WAS ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN
YOU'D GET INTO TROUBLE.
- I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
I HAD TO GO INTO
THE DEMON'S LAIR,
BECAUSE I COULDN'T IGNORE
A WOMAN WHO MIGHT BE GRIEVING.
- HMM?
IT'S NOT AS THOUGH I'M JEALOUS
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
HUH?
- SEE? WHAT'D I TELL YOU?
IT'S HAPPENING.
- IT MAKES ME HAPPY
THAT YOU WORRY.
YOUR CONCERN FOR ME MEANS MORE
THAN THAT OF ANY OTHER WOMAN.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU SAYING TO ME?
OH, NO.
WHAT'LL I DO?
- GO FOR IT, SANGO.
- SANGO?
HMM.
- HUH?
THAT HAND AGAIN!
WHY CAN'T HE TOUCH MY SHOULDERS
OR SOMEWHERE MORE ROMANTIC?!
[GROANING]
- CAN'T YOU GET YOUR MIND
OUT OF THE GUTTER?!
[GROANING]
- DON'T BLAME ME.
SHE WAS PRACTICALLY
BEGGING ME TO FONDLE HER.
- SURE. SURE.
YOU SHOULD SPEND MORE TIME
BRUSHING UP ON WOMEN'S FEELINGS
AND LESS TIME BRUSHING UP
ON THEIR BUNS.
- SEE, KAGOME?
DIDN'T I TELL YOU
THAT YOU WERE WRONG?
WELL, DIDN'T I?
- HMM. WHAT A DUMMY.
- OH, WELL, BETTER GET
THIS THING FIXED.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- GOING BACK HOME
AGAIN, KAGOME?
DO YOU LIKE THOSE TESTS
OF YOURS THAT MUCH?
OH, WELL, WHATEVER
MAKES YOU HAPPY.
I'VE GOT MY OWN PROBLEMS.
THIS CREEPY-LOOKING HUMAN FACE
FRUIT LEADS US TO TOGENKYO.
THE GUY THERE CALLS
HIMSELF A SAGE,
AND HE'S USING HUMANS TO MAKE
ANTI-AGING MEDICINE.
NEXT TIME...
DAMN. THE NIGHT OF
THE NEW MOON IS COMING.