- [PANTING]
THIS IS IT. THIS IS THE PLACE
THE MONK TOLD US ABOUT. HUH?
WHAT IS THIS, A HAIR BAND?
KIKYO. ARE YOU
REALLY STILL ALIVE?
- MY SPIRIT CANNOT REST IN PEACE
UNTIL I SEE YOU DEAD!
- DON'T DO THIS!
AAH! KIKYO!
[GRUNTS]
KIKYO!
- I DIED DESPISING YOU.
THE MOMENT I DIED, MY SOUL
WAS RENDERED PARALYZED.
AS LONG AS YOU LIVE,
I CANNOT BE SAVED.
- IS KIKYO SLEEPING?
SHE LOOKS SO FRAIL AND SAD.
[GASPS]
HMM?
- I SEE THAT MY BARRIER
WAS NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO PREVENT YOU
FROM FINDING ME.
- BARRIER? WHAT BARRIER?
I DON'T REMEMBER SEEING
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
ARE YOU THE ONE WHO'S BEEN
LURING THE SOULS OF WOMEN AWAY?
IT IS YOU, ISN'T IT?
YOU HAVE TO STOP.
YOU'VE GOT TO SET THEM FREE.
- IS HE NOT HERE WITH YOU?
- UH...
I CAME ON MY OWN.
INUYASHA SET OFF
TO FIND YOU EARLIER.
THAT'S RIGHT. HE MUST BE
TRYING TO COME HERE.
- TELL ME, WHAT IS
YOUR RELATIONSHIP?
- UH...
UH!
- THIS WILL END
YOUR INTERFERING.
- HUH? THEM AGAIN?
THE DEMONS THAT WERE MAKING OFF
WITH THE SOULS.
UH!
IT'S A SPIRIT SHIELD.
KIKYO MUST BE
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
KIKYO, IS IT REALLY YOU?
- I CAN'T MOVE!
- INUYASHA HAS COME.
- HUH?
- I FEAR HE HAS NOT COME
TO SAVE YOU.
HIS PURPOSE LIES
IN SEEING ME.
YOU WILL NOT INTERFERE.
- INTERFERE?
ARE YOU STILL PLANNING
TO DESTROY INUYASHA?
HE'S NOT YOUR ENEMY.
SOMEONE PITTED YOU AGAINST
EACH OTHER ON PURPOSE.
INUYASHA WOULD HAVE NEVER
TAKEN YOUR LIFE, KIKYO.
- HMM.
FROM YOUR COUNTENANCE, I GATHER
YOU EXPECT ME TO BE REJOICING.
- HUH?
- SOMEONE CAUSED
MY PREMATURE DEMISE.
WILL MY MURDERER'S DEATH
BRING ME BACK TO LIFE?
- I GUESS NOT.
- THE DEAD HAVE BUT ONE WISH--
TO WALK AMONGST THE LIVING
ONCE AGAIN.
A WISH THAT WILL
NEVER BE REALIZED.
HOWEVER, THIS DEAD WOMAN
CAN WISH FOR ONE THING.
I WISH FOR A HEART,
THE HEART OF THE MAN WHOM I
SHALL NEVER ALLOW TO FORGET ME.
THAT IS MY DESIRE.
- YOU'LL NEVER ALLOW HIM
TO FORGET ABOUT YOU?
YOU MEAN INUYASHA?
- IT IS CLEAR THAT INUYASHA
WISHES FOR MY DEATH.
THAT IS A GOOD THING,
BECAUSE IT MEANS HE FEELS
REMORSE FOR OUR DISPUTE.
LET HIM FEEL REMORSEFUL.
I SHALL NEVER ALLOW HIM
TO FORGET ABOUT ME.
TIME WILL NOT ADVANCE,
THUS ALLOWING ME
TO EXIST IN A DIMENSION
IN WHICH TIME IS FROZEN.
I CAN LIVE ON INSIDE HIS HEART
HERE IN MY FROZEN RE-CREATION.
- YOU'RE ALWAYS
ON INUYASHA'S MIND.
WHY CAN'T YOU BE SATISFIED
WITH THAT?
HE HASN'T FORGOTTEN YOU
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
HE THINKS OF YOU
ALL THE TIME.
ISN'T THAT GOOD ENOUGH?
[GASPS]
HMM.
- WHEN INUYASHA AND I PARTED,
WE DESPISED ONE ANOTHER.
THE LOVE YOU SPEAK OF
IS BUT A SHALLOW EMOTION,
AN EMOTION WHICH ONLY SERVED
TO DEEPEN THE HATRED.
NOTHING CAN RESOLVE
ONE'S DETERMINATION
FOR EXACTING VENGEANCE
IN THE WAY BITTERNESS CAN.
IF HE MUST LOVE, THEN LET HIM
LOVE MY CONSUMING RESENTMENT.
AND IN RETURN,
I SHALL LOVE HIS HEART
WHILE IT FALLS
INTO DEEP DESPAIR.
- NO, KIKYO, IT'S SENSELESS.
YOUR HATRED IS
TOTALLY POINTLESS. I--
- HMM?
- [PANTING]
- INUYASHA, YOU'VE
GOT TO TALK TO KIKYO.
PLEASE TELL HER
WHAT HAPPENED--
HOW NARAKU DECEIVED YOU.
INUYASHA?
- KIKYO.
- HE DIDN'T HEAR ME.
HE CAN'T EVEN SEE ME.
- SO YOU WERE THE ONE DOING IT--
GATHERING THE SOULS
OF THE DEAD WOMEN.
- MY BODY IS MOLDED
FROM THE EARTH AND
BONES AT MY GRAVESITE.
IT MUST BE SUSTAINED
BY HUMAN SOULS IF
I'M TO REMAIN HERE.
INUYASHA,
YOU MUST DESPISE ME.
I HAVE DRAWN IN THE SOULS OF THE
DEAD TO MAINTAIN MY PRESENCE,
AND IT IS MY HATRED OF YOU
THAT FUELS MY ACTIONS.
- THAT'S JUST LUDICROUS.
YOU MAY VERY WELL DESPISE ME,
BUT THE FEELING'S NOT MUTUAL.
KIKYO, I NEVER STOP
THINKING ABOUT YOU,
NOT EVEN FOR AN INSTANT.
- HMM.
- I THOUGHT SO. INUYASHA
HAS NEVER FORGOTTEN KIKYO.
SURE. WHY WOULD HE HAVE?
STILL, IT'S HARD TO HEAR IT
SAID OUT LOUD.
INUYASHA'S BEEN TAKEN AWAY
FROM ME.
WHAT AM I SAYING?
IT'S NOT LIKE HE WAS EVER
MY BOYFRIEND OR ANYTHING.
- I COULD NEVER HATE YOU
OR THINK LESS OF YOU.
IT'S YOUR SPIRIT I CARE FOR,
NOT YOUR APPEARANCE.
- TRULY, INUYASHA?
YOU WOULDN'T?
YOU WOULDN'T DESPISE ME
IF I USED THESE HANDS
TO STEAL THE LIFE FROM YOU?
- [GRUNTING]
- SHE'S KISSING HIM!
- INUYASHA,
AFTER MEETING YOU,
I RENOUNCED MY POSITION
AS A SHRINE PRIESTESS.
I BECAME AN ORDINARY WOMAN.
I LONGED TO EMBRACE YOU
LIKE THIS WHEN I WAS ALIVE.
- INUYASHA, YOU'RE
GOING TO TAKE HER BACK.
SURE YOU ARE.
IT'S ONLY TO BE EXPECTED.
WHAT AM I DOING HERE
WATCHING THEM LIKE THIS?
I'M SUCH A FOOL.
OH, GREAT.
NOW I'M PROBABLY
GOING TO START CRYING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT AN IDIOT I AM.
- KIKYO'S SCENT
IS SO FAMILIAR.
HER FRAGRANCE IS
JUST AS IT USED TO BE.
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE
IS THAT SHE HAS NO WARMTH.
HER BODY IS COLD FROM DEATH,
AND SHE'S SAD AND LONELY.
- WE ARE UNABLE TO TURN BACK
THE HANDS OF TIME,
SO PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO EMBRACE YOU A LITTLE LONGER.
- I CAN'T SAVE YOU.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
TO HELP YOU,
EXCEPT STAY LIKE THIS.
IF ONLY TIME
COULD STAND STILL.
- WOULD YOU AGREE TO THAT
IF I DID STOP TIME?
- YES. I DON'T CARE,
AS LONG AS--
AS LONG AS I'M WITH YOU.
- UHH! I CAN'T WATCH.
I'D BE HAPPY TO LEAVE YOU TWO
ALONE IF YOU'D JUST RELEASE ME.
I'LL JUST GO CRAWL UNDER A ROCK
OR SOMETHING LIKE--
HEY! ARE YOU LISTENING?
- INUYASHA,
I WILL NEVER LET YOU GO.
COME WITH ME
TO THE DEPTHS OF HELL.
- HE'S BEING DRAGGED DOWN
WITH HER!
INUYASHA, SNAP TO IT!
YOU'VE GOTTA GET OUT OF THERE!
IT'S NO USE.
HE'S UNCONSCIOUS.
LISTEN, KIKYO, 'CAUSE I KNOW
THAT YOU CAN HEAR ME.
THAT'S NOT FAIR. INUYASHA SAID
HE WANTED TO BE WITH YOU.
I DIDN'T HEAR HIM SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT WANTING TO DIE WITH YOU.
INUYASHA'S GOING AFTER NARAKU
FOR DECEIVING YOU BOTH
50 YEARS AGO.
HE STILL HAS THINGS TO DO.
INUYASHA WANTS TO LIVE TO FIGHT
NARAKU MORE THAN ANYTHING,
AND HE'S DETERMINED TO STAY
ALIVE UNTIL HE FACES HIM
AND AVENGES YOUR DEATH!
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M SAYING?
AAH!
OH, KIKYO...
- AND WHAT IF HE DOES
EXACT REVENGE?
WILL THAT SERVE
TO REVIVE ME?
COME, INUYASHA.
COME, RATHER THAN STAYING HERE
AND LIVING WITH MY MEMORY.
YOU AND I SHARE
THE SAME DESIRES.
- YOU'RE DOWNRIGHT EVIL!
THE POOR GUY IS UNCONSCIOUS,
REMEMBER?
OTHERWISE
HE'D NEVER FOLLOW YOU.
DO US ALL A FAVOR
AND LET GO OF INUYASHA!
I'M TELLING YOU!
HANDS OFF OF HIM!
- UH!
[HEART BEATING]
- AAH!
THIS GIRL IS TAKING MY SPIRIT
ONCE AGAIN.
I MUST HURRY BEFORE THIS BODY IS
COMPLETELY EMPTIED.
INUYASHA, COME.
- WAKE UP! DON'T LET HER
TAKE YOU, INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
WAKE UP, INUYASHA!
- THAT'S KAGOME'S VOICE.
KAGOME?
IS SHE...HERE?
KAGOME!
HUH? KAGOME!
[GRUNTS]
KAGOME, WHAT IN THE WORLD DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING HERE?
- ME? I'M THE ONE WHO SHOULD BE
ASKING THAT QUESTION.
- WELL, UH,
IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN.
[GRUNTS]
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO HER?
- DOES THAT GIRL MEAN MORE
TO YOU THAN I DO?
- UH...MM...UH...
NOW, WAIT, KIKYO!
LISTEN TO ME!
- INUYASHA, NEVER FORGET.
REMEMBER THE FEEL OF MY LIPS
AGAINST YOURS,
FOR IT WAS REAL.
- NEVER FORGET.
- GOOD-BYE, KIKYO.
- HMM!
- HUH? HEY, WAIT!
- STAY AWAY!
- WHAT ARE YOU MAD AT ME FOR?
- WE REALLY NEED TO TALK,
INUYASHA.
HOW ABOUT YOU LOOK FOR
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
ON YOUR OWN?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
'CAUSE I DON'T THINK I'LL
BE ABLE TO HELP YOU ANYMORE.
- WHERE IS ALL THIS STUFF
COMING FROM?
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN LOCATE THE JEWELS.
I NEED YOU TO HELP ME.
- IS THAT ALL I'M GOOD FOR,
FINDING JEWELS?
THAT REALLY IS THE ONLY REASON
YOU NEED ME.
- [GRUNTS]
- WHAT AM I RAMBLING ON ABOUT?
FORGET IT.
JUST FORGET I SAID
ANY OF THAT.
I GUESS IT'S JUST THE THOUGHT
OF BEING ON MY OWN IN THE WORLD.
IT'S KIND OF A LONELY PROSPECT.
- YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
I'M RIGHT HERE WITH YOU.
UNLESS YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
WITH ME ANYMORE.
- INUYASHA, I GET IT.
YOU WEREN'T ABLE TO SEE ME THERE
AT ALL, WERE YOU?
- UH...
- I SAW THE WHOLE THING
BETWEEN YOU AND KIKYO.
- UH...YOU MEAN--
- THAT'S RIGHT,
FROM START TO FINISH.
SO I'D APPRECIATE IT IF YOU'D
LEAVE ME ALONE FOR A BIT.
- HEY, DON'T DO THIS TO ME!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "THE WHOLE THING"?
WAIT, KAGOME!
WHAT WAS I DOING
WHEN YOU SAW ME?
UHH!
WAIT! TELL ME, KAGOME!
- SIT!
- AAH!
- I MEAN THE WHOLE THING,
ALL OF IT!
I HAD A FRONT ROW SEAT!
[SIGHS]
I'M GOING HOME.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU FIND HER?
WHAT'S GOING ON, INUYASHA?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
DOWN ON THE GROUND?
HAVE YOU SEEN KAGOME AROUND?
- I RECOGNIZE THIS POSITION,
MEANING KAGOME MUST BE
SOMEWHERE NEARBY.
- AND BY THE DEPTH OF THIS HOLE,
I'D SAY SHE'S FEISTY AS EVER.
- MM...
KIKYO, IS IT REALLY YOU?
- WHAT AILS YOU, KAEDE?
DO YOU FEAR YOUR OWN SISTER?
- YOU MISUNDERSTAND.
I HEARD YE HAD FALLEN
FROM THE CLIFF.
I DIDN'T IMAGINE
YE WOULD SURVIVE.
- YOU WERE CORRECT.
I AM DEAD.
YET, SOMETHING LEFT UNDONE
IN THIS WORLD
KEEPS ME FROM MOVING ON.
- DO YE STILL REMAIN RESOLVED
TO TAKE INUYASHA'S LIFE?
- INUYASHA.
I SAW HIM JUST MOMENTS AGO
AND ALMOST SUCCEEDED IN WRINGING
THE LIFE FROM HIM.
SPEAK TO ME, KAEDE.
TELL ME ALL YOU HAVE TO OFFER
ABOUT THIS NARAKU PERSON.
- MY SOUL IS RANCID
TO THE CORE,
YET IT STILL HOLDS VALUE.
FEAST ON MY FLESH.
I MUST POSSESS
MY FORMER ABILITY.
THEN THE JEWEL WILL BE MINE,
NOT TO MENTION
THE LOVELY MAIDEN KIKYO.
FEAST ON ME, DEMONS.
DEVOUR ME!
AND IN EXCHANGE, BESTOW ME
WITH YOUR MOBILITY AND STRENGTH!
- EVERYTHING WAS STARTED BY
THE EVIL DESIGNS OF ONIGUMO.
HE CALLED FORTH THE DEMONS
AND WAS DEVOURED BY THEM.
THUS WAS BORN
THE MONSTER NARAKU.
- SO, IT ALL BEGAN WITH ONIGUMO,
THAT BANDIT.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
HE USED TO SAY THAT
THE SACRED JEWEL
GROWS IN BEAUTY
WHEN IT IS TAINTED
WITH MALICE.
- HE FUELED THE HATRED
BETWEEN INUYASHA AND MYSELF,
THEN ATTEMPTED TO STEAL
THE JEWEL THAT HAD BEEN
TAINTED IN THE PROCESS.
- LISTEN, KIKYO.
INUYASHA WAS SERIOUSLY WOUNDED
BY NARAKU ONCE AGAIN.
SO, PLEASE...
- I HAVE HEARD ENOUGH.
I ONLY CAME
BECAUSE I THOUGHT I SHOULD KNOW
THE CIRCUMSTANCES OF MY DEATH.
I NOTICED THAT INUYASHA
HAS CHANGED.
HIS FACE HAS
A CERTAIN SOFTNESS.
LONG AGO, HIS EYES
WERE MUCH COLDER,
AND HE THOUGHT HE COULD AFFORD
TO PLACE HIS TRUST IN NO ONE.
- KAGOME IS A STRANGE CHILD.
LITTLE BY LITTLE,
SHE HAS BEEN ABLE TO HEAL
THE WOUNDS OF HIS HEART.
- SO SHE IS
THE ONE RESPONSIBLE.
IT WAS SHE WHO CHANGED INUYASHA.
IF I HAD LIVED,
IT IS I WHO WOULD HAVE TENDED
TO THE WOUNDS IN HIS SOUL.
- PLEASE, KIKYO,
CAN YE NOT BREAK AWAY
FROM THE PAST AND MOVE ON?
- WE SHALL MEET AGAIN.
- [SIGHS]
HOW LONG WILL YE WANDER
THE EARTH, KIKYO?
- AAH! UHH...UHH...UH!
OHH...AH!
HMM!
- AND SO SHE HAS LEFT US
ONCE AGAIN.
INUYASHA, KAGOME WAS NOT ACTING
HER USUAL SELF.
EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN YOU AND KIKYO?
- THE SAME THING THAT GOES
ON WHEN YOU'RE WITH A WOMAN.
- AAH!
GHASTLY!
YOU MEAN YOU DID THAT
RIGHT IN FRONT OF KAGOME?
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD EXPLAIN
WHAT YOU DO WITH WOMEN!
- NOTHING.
- DO YOU THINK KAGOME
WILL EVER COME BACK?
SHE LOOKED AWFULLY UPSET.
- HMM...
- I NEVER STOP THINKING ABOUT
YOU, NOT EVEN FOR AN INSTANT!
I SPOKE THE TRUTH.
- REMEMBER THE FEEL OF MY LIPS
AGAINST YOURS,
FOR IT WAS REAL.
- AND MY WORDS WERE REAL.
- DOES THAT GIRL MEAN MORE
TO YOU THAN I DO?
- UH...UM...
- NOW WHAT COURSE WILL YOU TAKE,
INUYASHA?
KIKYO CAN'T HAVE
GOTTEN TOO FAR YET.
WILL YOU FOLLOW?
- KAGOME IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN KIKYO IS,
SO HURRY AND MAKE UP
WITH KAGOME, INUYASHA.
- HMM. WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH ME?
I WAS IN SUCH A DAZE,
I FORGOT ALL MY THINGS
BACK HERE.
HEY, CAN ANYONE UP THERE
HEAR ME?
- WHAT WILL YOU DO, INUYASHA?
- WHICH GIRL WILL YOU CHOOSE?
- ANSWER!
- WHICH ONE?
- UH...
I DON'T SUPPOSE I COULD HAVE
BOTH OF THEM.
- MM! YOU TWO-TIMING...
- WELL, IT'S A COMMON PROBLEM
BETWEEN MEN SUCH AS OURSELVES.
AND IT'S ONE THING TO HAVE BOTH,
BUT ANOTHER TO KEEP IT A SECRET,
FOR IF EITHER GIRL
WERE TO FIND OUT--
- SIT!
- AAH!
- THAT'S RIGHT, BIG SIT. HMM?
- [GROANING]
- THEY SAY THAT KARMA
INCLUDES BAD THOUGHTS.
- JUST AS WELL. IT SPARED HIM
A GREAT DEAL OF GRIEF.
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- THE PEOPLE IN A NEARBY TOWN
MAKE A LIVING
EXTERMINATING DEMONS.
IF WE GO THERE, WE MAY BE ABLE
TO FIND OUT SOMETHING
ABOUT THE JEWEL SHARDS.
BUT IT SEEMS THAT
WE AREN'T THE ONLY ONES
WHO HAVE FIGURED THAT OUT.
THE EXTERMINATORS FALL PREY
TO ONE OF THEIR OWN KIND
WHO HAS BEEN POSSESSED
BY A DEMON,
AND A SISTER AND BROTHER
FALL INTO A TRAP.
THE ENTIRE DECEPTION HAS BEEN
LAIN BY NONE OTHER THAN NARAKU.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!