- [GASPS]
I KNOW THIS ANSWER.
THESE PROBLEMS ARE A SNAP.
- [CHUCKLES]
WELL DONE.
WELL DONE!
OH, REMARKABLE.
VERY NICE, KAGOME.
YOU GOT A PERFECT SCORE!
- WAY TO GO, KAGOME!
- YOU'LL GET INTO
HIGH SCHOOL NO PROBS.
- YOU GO, GIRLFRIEND!
- CONGRATULATIONS!
- HOW'D YOU DO IT?!
- THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
THIS ISN'T A DREAM.
IT'S REALLY HAPPENING!
IT WAS A DREAM.
[SIGHS]
- WHAT?!
YOU'RE GONNA GO
BACK HOME AGAIN?!
- CALM DOWN.
IT'S NOT WORTH LOSING
YOUR VOICE OVER.
- DON'T YOU REALIZE
WHAT AN IMPORTANT TIME
THIS IS, KAGOME?
- OF COURSE I DO,
BUT I NEED TO STUDY
FOR AN IMPORTANT EXAM
THAT I'VE GOTTA TAKE.
- EXAM?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- IT'S SHORT FOR EXAMINATION,
AS IN A TEST.
- HMPH!
"AS IN A TEST," SHE SAYS.
- COME ON.
GIVE ME 3 DAYS,
'CAUSE I NEED TO REVIEW FIRST.
- THINGS ARE SO
COMPLICATED FOR KAGOME.
- YEAH.
IT WOULD BE EASIER IF SHE COULD
STAY WITH US ALL THE TIME.
- 3 DAYS, HUH?
- DO YOU LIKE THESE TESTS
THAT MUCH, KAGOME?
- AAH!
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
HUH?
- HMM?
- THIS MIGHT NOT
BE THE BEST TIME,
BUT I'D LIKE TO HAVE 3 DAYS
SO THAT I CAN GO BACK
TO MY VILLAGE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
- BACK TO THE DEMON
SLAYER'S VILLAGE?
- YES.
I NEED TIME TO GET REPAIRS
DONE ON MY HIRAIKOTSU.
- [SCREAMING]
- I'VE USED IT IN
A LOT OF BATTLES LATELY.
- AAH!
3 DAYS, THEN,
BUT THAT'S ALL.
- YES!
THAT MEANS I CAN GO HOME, TOO.
- SORRY ABOUT THIS.
I'LL RETURN TO KAEDE'S VILLAGE
3 DAYS FROM NOW.
COME ON.
LET'S GO, KILALA.
- WELL, NOW THAT SHE'S AWAY,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO TAKE IT EASY
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
ARE YOU SAYING YOU
CAN'T TAKE IT EASY
WHEN SANGO'S AROUND?
- NOPE.
UH, I MEAN,
NOTHING OF THE SORT.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE INUYASHA
GAVE IN SO EASILY.
- HMM.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- WHO, ME? OH, NOTHING.
- FINE. THEN LET'S GO.
- HUH?
HEY, WAIT FOR ME.
- [PANTING]
THINK I SHOULD BE SAFE NOW.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
- WHERE YOU GOING?
- SPARE ME, PLEASE!
- I KINDLY TOOK YOU
IN AS MY APPRENTICE,
AND YOU HAVE THE GALL
TO ESCAPE FROM TRAINING?
- NO!
- YOU WERE SUFFERING
FROM EXPOSURE AND HUNGER.
THEN YOU WERE FORCED
TO FIGHT IN THE WAR,
BUT YOU DIDN'T WANT
TO DIE A MISERABLE DEATH.
I HAPPEN TO KNOW THIS
BECAUSE YOU TOLD ME.
- SATE, I BEG YOU TO FORGIVE ME.
- YOU WERE SICK OF THE WORLD.
THAT'S WHY I AGREED TO BRING
YOU HERE TO TOGENKYO--
TO TRAIN YOU TO BECOME A SAGE.
[GROWLS]
- I DON'T WANT TO BECOME
A SAGE ANYMORE!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF
THIS EERIE PLACE!
[CHUCKLES]
- YOU PITIFUL FOOL.
- [SCREAMING]
- [SPITS]
[LAUGHS]
- HMM?
HMM.
- LOOK AT THIS HEAVY FOG.
- IT'S NOT JUST FOG.
HMM?
- WHAT IS THIS?
THIS IS THE CREEPIEST-LOOKING
FRUIT I'VE EVER SEEN.
- LOOK AT THAT!
A HUMAN FRUIT.
- HUMAN FRUIT?
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
- NIMENKA, A DEMON TREE.
USES HUMANS AS NOURISHMENT,
SO ITS FRUIT RESEMBLES
HUMAN FACES.
- SO THAT THING'S
THE FRUIT OF A DEMON TREE?
- YES.
AND CONSIDERING HOW MANY OF
THEM ARE FLOATING DOWNSTREAM,
THE DEMONIC TREE HAS
TO BE EXTREMELY LARGE.
- HUH, THERE'S A LOT OF UNREST.
WITH ALL THE BATTLES GOING ON,
THERE'S NO SHORTAGE OF BODIES
TO BE HAD FOR FERTILIZER.
- POSSIBLY.
BUT THERE ISN'T ANY FIGHTING
THAT DEEP IN THE MOUNTAINS.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
COME ON.
LET'S GO CHECK IT OUT.
- HMM.
THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE GOING HOME.
- I'D BE TOO WORRIED
TO STUDY, ANYWAY.
BESIDES, I'VE STILL
GOT 3 DAYS TILL THE TEST.
- SO MUCH FOR TAKING A BREAK.
- YOU FORGETTING SOMEONE?
YOU CAN'T JUST IGNORE ME!
- STOP DAWDLING.
I'M IN A RUSH.
- LET'S HURRY AND GET
THIS OVER WITH.
- HUH, SOME FRIENDS.
HUH?
- THE DEMON TREE OF
THE HUMAN-FACED FRUITS
MUST BE HIGH UP ABOVE.
- AT THE TOP OF THIS CLIFF?
- LOOK.
IS THAT IT?
- INCREDIBLE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
SUCH A COLOSSAL
HUMAN-FACED FRUIT TREE
AND THIS OMINOUS DEMON AURA.
- WHICH MEANS IT
MUST HAVE CONSUMED
A LOT OF HUMANS ALREADY.
- ALL RIGHT.
- INUYASHA.
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
- WHAT ELSE?
I'M GONNA GO UP THERE
AND CHOP DOWN THAT DEMON TREE.
- WE'LL GO WITH YOU.
- WAIT FOR US.
- I AIN'T WASTING A WHOLE DAY
HAULING EACH OF YOU
LUGS UP THIS CLIFF.
- COME ON.
- INUYASHA WANTS TO
GET THIS OVER WITH
BEFORE THE SUN GOES DOWN.
- HUH?
- THE LUNAR MONTH
STARTS TONIGHT.
- LUNAR MONTH?
THE NEW MOON!
THE NIGHT INUYASHA LOSES HIS
POWERS AND BECOMES HUMAN.
NO WONDER HE'S RUSHING.
- EHH...
NO FRUIT OF LONGEVITY YET.
HOW I TIRE OF EATING
THESE ALL THE TIME.
- ARE YOU THE ONE WHO'S
FEEDING THIS DEMON TREE?
- WHO WANTS TO KNOW?
- I DON'T PICK UP ANY
DEMON SCENT FROM HIM,
BUT HE REEKS OF DEAD MEN.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH ME?
- I AIN'T GONNA WASTE
MY TIME TALKING TO YOU,
BUT I AM GONNA CHOP DOWN
THAT DAMN TREE.
STAY AWAY, OR ELSE.
- OH?
OR ELSE WHAT?
- I'LL HACK YOU DOWN AS WELL.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
THAT FLABBY CRETIN.
THE TETSUSAIGA
DIDN'T WORK ON HIM.
THIS CALLS FOR SOMETHING
MORE SERIOUS.
MY WINDSCAR!
EVEN THAT DIDN'T WORK.
- OH, A DEMON, ARE YOU?
AND A FOOL.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE
YOU COME FROM,
BUT DID YOU THINK YOU
COULD DEFEAT A SAGE?
- YOU'RE A SAGE?
- CORRECT.
I AM THE SAGE OF TOGENKYO.
TOKAJIN!
- THE GOURD IS GETTING BIGGER.
[GRUNTS]
- WRONG.
IT'S NOT GROWING BIGGER.
YOU'RE SHRINKING.
- HUH?
MY TETSUSAIGA!
DAMN, IT'S NO ILLUSION.
ARE YOU TELLING ME
THAT YOU REALLY ARE A SAGE?
- STOP MAKING ME REPEAT MYSELF.
- IF YOU'RE A SAGE,
WHY DO YOU STOOP TO THIS?
- WISH TO GO INSIDE
AND FOUND OUT?
- [SCREAMING]
- [LAUGHS]
THIS DEMON WILL MAKE FOR
EXCELLENT FERTILIZER.
- [GRUNTING]
- COME ON, HANG IN THERE,
SHIPPO!
IT'S NOT MUCH FURTHER.
- SHIPPO, I'M QUITE IMPRESSED.
YOU TURNED OUT TO BE
STRONG AFTER ALL.
- [GRUNTING]
- I'D FORGOTTEN THAT
TONIGHT WAS A NEW MOON.
WHEN THE SUN SETS,
INUYASHA WILL TEMPORARILY
BECOME A REGULAR HUMAN.
- KAGOME!
SORRY.
- HMM?
[SCREAMING]
HANG ON!
- [SIGHING]
- [GRUNTING AND GROANING]
- IT LOOKS AS THOUGH
WE'VE STUMBLED ACROSS
SOMEBODY'S HIDDEN MANSION.
- LOOK AT THAT.
WONDER WHAT IT IS.
[GASPS]
IT'S A MAN!
- THERE ARE OTHERS, TOO!
- WHAT ON EARTH
IS GOING ON HERE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- DO YOU THINK THIS
IS WHERE THEY LIVE?
- YOUR GUESS IS AS GOOD AS MINE.
- [GASPS]
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
ARE GETTING BIGGER.
- OH, THE MINIATURE VILLAGE
IS GROWING LARGER, TOO.
- NO, THE VILLAGE
ISN'T GETTING BIGGER.
WE'RE SHRINKING.
- [SCREAMING]
- [GRUNTING]
- WHERE ARE WE?
- THOSE ARE THE TINY MEN
THAT WE SAW WALKING AROUND.
- WHICH COULD ONLY MEAN...
- THAT WE'RE INSIDE
THE MINIATURE VILLAGE AS WELL.
- WHAT? WHAT'LL WE DO?
DO WE HAVE TO LIVE HERE FOR
THE REST OF OUR LIVES, OR WHAT?
- WE HAVE TO FIND
A WAY OUT OF HERE.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT INUYASHA,
NOT TO MENTION THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- KAGOME'S RIGHT.
- HOW DO WE GET OUT
OF HERE, THOUGH?
- FIRST WE HAVE TO FIND
OUT WHAT'S GOING ON.
LET'S GO TALK TO
THE MEN OVER THERE
AND SEE WHAT THEY HAVE
TO SAY ABOUT THIS.
- EXCUSE ME.
COULD YOU EXPLAIN
WHAT YOU'RE ALL DOING HERE?
- THIS WORLD ISN'T REAL.
DO YOU REALIZE THAT?
- HELLO?
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
- PLEASE STOP DISTURBING US.
WE'RE IN THE MIDST OF TRAINING.
- PARDON?
- YES.
WE ARE ALL IN THE PROCESS
OF TRAINING TO BECOME SAGES.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
TRAINING TO BECOME SAGES?
- WHEN WE BECOME
AS STRONG AS SAGES,
WE SHALL BE RELEASED,
AND MASTER TOKAJIN
WILL BESTOW US
WITH THE FRUIT OF LONGEVITY.
- TOKAJIN?
- IS TOKAJIN THE VILLAIN WHO
TRAPPED YOU INSIDE THIS PLACE?
- MASTER TOKAJIN IS OUR SAVIOR
BECAUSE HE RESCUED US
FROM HUNGER AND WAR.
DO NOT SPEAK ILL OF HIM.
- [GASPS]
- NO MATTER HOW I LOOK AT IT,
IT'S JUST A RUSTY OLD SWORD.
YET I AM CERTAIN
THE SWORD TRANSFORMED
WHEN THAT YOUNG DEMON
WIELDED IT.
[SIGHS]
OH, WELL.
[GROANING]
- HUH?
AAH!
HUH?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I DROPPED THE TETSUSAIGA.
I MUST BE GETTING WEAK ALREADY,
SEEING AS I DIDN'T
TRANSFORM INTO A DEMON.
STILL, FINE PLACE I'VE
GOTTEN MYSELF TRAPPED IN.
MY COAT IS STARTING TO DISSOLVE.
I CAN'T WASTE TIME IN HERE.
I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE
TO CLAW MY WAY OUT.
IRON-REAPER SOUL-STEALER!
HUH?
IMPOSSIBLE.
I BARELY SCRATCHED IT.
[SCREAMING]
IF ONLY I HAD THE TETSUSAIGA,
THIS WOULD BE A PIECE OF CAKE!
DAMN IT!
DAMN HIM!
I'LL TEACH HIM WHEN
I GET OUT OF HERE!
[GASPS]
MY CLAWS.
OH, NO.
MY POWER'S DISAPPEARING.
- HUH?
WHAT'S THAT?
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
TWO OF THEM.
ONE SHARD WAS ALL I REQUIRED
TO DEFLECT A DEMON'S SWORD.
WITH THIS MANY, MY BODY WILL
BE A PLATE OF ARMOR!
[LAUGHING]
- DAMN.
THE LIQUID IS RISING.
I'D BETTER COME UP
WITH SOMETHING FAST,
OR I'LL BE MELTED.
THINK. THINK!
- IS THAT GONNA GET THEM
ANY CLOSER TO BECOMING SAGES?
- I'M NOT SURE.
IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING THAT
REACHING SAGE-LIKE
ENLIGHTENMENT
REQUIRES PHYSICAL STRENGTH,
BUT IT'S SPIRITUAL PROWESS
THAT IS THE MOST
CRUCIAL ATTRIBUTE.
- YOU THERE.
- HUH?
- THE 3 OF YOU DON'T SEEM TO
BE FROM AROUND THESE PARTS.
- A SAMURAI!
- YOU DON'T SEEM LIKE
THE OTHERS EITHER.
- AS YOU CAN SEE, I'M A WARRIOR.
I WAS AMONG THE VANQUISHED,
AND THEN I ESCAPED
INTO THE VALLEY,
ONLY TO BE CAPTURED BY TOKAJIN.
- BUT AREN'T YOU GOING TO TRAIN
TO BECOME A SAGE
LIKE THE OTHERS?
- NO.
ONCE YOU MASTER EVEN
A TINY BIT OF SPIRITUAL POWER,
YOU BECOME FODDER FOR NIMENKA
THE DEMON TREE.
- [GASPS]
- I SAW IT WITH MY OWN EYES.
TOKAJIN WAS TALKING
TO THE DEMON TREE
OF THE HUMAN-FACED FRUITS.
- NIMENKA, ISN'T IT TIME YET?
WHEN WILL YOU BARE
THE FRUIT OF LONGEVITY?
- NOT FOR A WHILE.
FIRST YOU MUST FEED ME
MANY MORE SOULS OF SAGES.
- BUT YOU MUST UNDERSTAND.
THERE AREN'T THAT
MANY SAGES AROUND.
- SILENCE!
SPARE ME THE EXCUSES
AND DO AS I SAY.
- VERY WELL, THEN.
BUT, DEMON TREE,
YOU ARE INDEED NOISY.
- WHAT?
- I'LL JUST REMOVE THIS
SO YOU WON'T BE ABLE TALK.
- NO!
STOP!
- I'LL KEEP IT SAFE FOR YOU.
DON'T WORRY.
I PROMISE I'LL BRING YOU
THE SOULS OF SAGES WITHOUT FAIL.
WHO'S THERE?!
ANOTHER VANQUISHED SOLDIER,
I PRESUME.
- [SCREAMING]
TRAIN HARD WHILE
YOU'RE IN THERE.
[GRUNTING]
- [SCREAMING]
- IT WAS PROBABLY A SACRED
JEWEL SHARD THAT YOU SAW.
- HMM.
IT'S FAINT, BUT I DEFINITELY
SENSE THE PRESENCE
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
- WHAT A HORRIBLY
WICKED SAGE SHE IS.
- I HAVE HEARD THAT UNLESS
A MAN RENOUNCES THE WORLD
AND BECOMES A HERMIT,
IT IS NOT POSSIBLE TO REACH
THE ENLIGHTENMENT OF A SAGE.
- AND THAT IS PRECISELY WHY
THESE MEN CANNOT BECOME SAGES.
- HMM.
THOSE POOR MEN.
THEY'RE TRAINING ONLY TO END UP
AS NOURISHMENT FOR
THE DEMON TREE.
- ALL OF THOSE MEN
TURNED DEAF EARS TO ME.
- MAYBE WE CAN TRY
TALKING TO THEM.
- NO.
IT'LL SERVE NO PURPOSE.
THERE'S NO WAY OUT.
SO, IT'S USELESS.
- NO WAY.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
THAT WE CAN DO.
THERE HAS TO BE
A WAY OUT OF HERE.
INUYASHA, I JUST
HOPE YOU'RE SAFE.
- [GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
DAMN, THAT HURTS.
I CAN FEEL PAIN NOW.
THIS IS WHY I HATE BEING MORTAL.
HUH!
HOW CAN I GET OUT OF HERE?
HUH?
MY SHEATH IS CALLING
THE TETSUSAIGA.
HMM.
THAT MEANS MY SWORD IS CLOSE BY.
ALL RIGHT.
I MIGHT GET OUT OF HERE YET.
COME HERE, TETSUSAIGA.
- I SUPPOSE I'LL HEAD BACK.
- HUH?
THAT RUSTY OLD SWORD AGAIN.
- THAT'S THE WAY, BIG GUY.
GET ME OUT.
KEEP IT COMING.
- [GRUNTING]
- TIME TO BLOW THIS GOURD.
- IT'S YOU!
- YEAH, GENIUS.
HOPE YOU GOT YOUR WILL SIGNED.
- YOU'RE THAT DEMON KID
I CAPTURED EARLIER.
- WHO WERE YOU EXPECTING?
IT'S PAYBACK TIME!
- [GROANING]
OW!
THAT HURT.
- [GASPS]
YOU'VE GOT A JEWEL SHARD!
- WHY, YOU!
YOU WON'T GET AWAY!
- WHERE'D YOU GET
THAT JEWEL SHARD?
DON'T TELL ME.
- BE PREPARED,
FOR YOU ARE THE ONE
WHO IS ABOUT TO PERISH!
[ROARING]
- TRY ME!
- [LAUGHING]
THE JEWEL SHARD HOLDS
TREMENDOUS POWERS.
IT IS INVINCIBLE.
- HOW? HOW CAN WE
GET OUT OF HERE?
IT MIGHT ALREADY BE
TOO LATE FOR INUYASHA.
- NO LUCK, KAGOME!
THERE'S NO WAY OUT OF HERE!
- NOTHING BUT WALLS
ALL THE WAY AROUND.
- OH, NO.
- [GRUNTING]
IT'S USELESS.
EITHER WE BECOME SAGES
AND GET FED TO THE DEMON TREE
OF HUMAN-FACED FRUITS,
OR WE STAY HERE AND PERISH.
THOSE ARE OUR ONLY CHOICES.
- NO, YOU'RE WRONG.
- I WISH I WAS WRONG.
THERE IS NO ESCAPING THIS HELL.
- [SHUDDERING]
- MAYBE IT ISN'T REAL.
IF IT'S A DREAM,
PLEASE LET THIS NIGHTMARE END!
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- THIS IS A DREAM.
NOTHING BUT A DREAM.
SHIPPO, PINCH ME.
OW!
IT'S NOT A DREAM AFTER ALL.
INUYASHA, IT'S THE NEW MOON,
AND YOU'VE TURNED INTO A HUMAN.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU
CAN DEFEAT THAT SAGE
WITH HIS CREEPY POWERS.
DON'T BE SO STUPID.
YOU CAN'T SACRIFICE
YOUR LIFE FOR ME.
NO, INUYASHA, DON'T DO IT.
NEXT TIME...
"FATEFUL NIGHT IN TOGENKYO,
PART TWO."
PLEASE, LET THIS NIGHT END SOON.