>> I HAD CAUGHT A TERRIBLE COLD
AND RETURNED TO MY PRESENT-DAY
WORLD TO GET BETTER.
ALL MY FRIENDS CAME TO VISIT ME,
AND THAT'S WHEN I LEARNED ABOUT
THE BIG COMPREHENSION TEST
WE WERE ALL GOING TO HAVE
THE FOLLOWING DAY.
>> HOJO, I NEED YOU TO HELP ME.
I NEED YOU TO HELP ME STUDY.
>> MY FEVER WOULDN'T GO DOWN,
THOUGH.
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT I WOULDN'T
GET BETTER IN TIME FOR
THE TEST...
>> HERE.
IT'S MEDICINE.
DRINK UP.
>> INUYASHA MADE ME A SPECIAL
POTION HIS MOTHER HAD
TAUGHT HIM TO MAKE, AND I WAS
ABLE TO GET THROUGH THE
TEST SOMEHOW.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
>> MMM, AHH, MMM.
THE WEATHER'S GREAT AND I
FEEL FANTASTIC.
I'M FINALLY OVER THAT NASTY
COLD, TOO, AND I MADE IT
THROUGH THE TEST.
I OWE YOU BIG TIME, INUYASHA.
>> YEAH. WHATEVER.
>> THANK YOU.
HONESTLY.
>> HA.
YOU SAID THAT ALREADY.
IF YOU'RE ALL BETTER, THEN
I WON'T BOTHER HANGING AROUND
ANY LONGER.
>> SAY, INUYASHA.
>> YEAH? WHAT IS IT NOW?
>> WANNA GO SHOPPING WITH ME?
>> HUH?
HEH.
HOW COME I GET STUCK
BEING DRAGGED ALL OVER YOUR
VILLAGE LIKE THIS?
>> TAKE IT EASY.
WE'VE GOT A LONG JOURNEY
AHEAD OF US, SO WE HAVE TO
STOCK UP ON SUPPLIES.
>> WASN'T IT YOU THAT TOLD ME
NOT TO GO OUT IN PUBLIC
LAST TIME I WAS HERE?
>> YEAH, BUT THAT WAS THEN
AND THIS IS NOW.
[GIGGLES]
>> HMPH.
SHE'S GOT A LINE FOR EVERYTHING.
>> [THINKING] IT ALMOST FEELS
LIKE WE'RE ON A DATE, WALKING
AROUND TOGETHER LIKE THIS.
HUH?
UH--
>> [SNIFFING]
>> HUH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> HEY, KAGOME.
THIS IS FOOD, RIGHT?
>> [GIGGLES]
>> LET'S START WITH YOU,
INUYASHA.
WHAT DO YOU WANT MOST?
>> NINJA FOOD.
OH...
>> INSTANT NOODLES, HUH?
THIS WAY.
>> HEY!
[GROANS]
WOW, LOOK AT 'EM ALL.
>> WHICH ONE DO YOU WANT?
>> HMM.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
A TOUGH DECISION.
HMM.
MMM.
>> SO YOU THINK MAYBE
WE BOUGHT TOO MUCH?
>> [GRUNTING]
THAT'S AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
>> HUH?
>> UHH!
THANKS FOR NOTHING!
WHAT'D YOU STOP LIKE THAT FOR?
>> LOOK.
>> HUH?
UHH!
HEY!
HOW COME WE GOTTA HIDE IN HERE?
>> IT'S SOTA.
WHAT DO YOU THINK HE'S UP TO?
>> HUH?
>> LOOKING FOR A GIFT?
DO YOU SEE ANYTHING YOU LIKE?
>> MMM...
>> WELL, YOU LET ME KNOW IF YOU
DECIDE ON ANYTHING.
[GIGGLES]
>> [GROANS]
[GROANS]
>> WHAT'S HE DOING OVER THERE?
>> DON'T KNOW.
>> HUH?
>> [GIRLS GIGGLING]
>> [INDISTINCT]
>> YEAH, AND THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I ACCIDENTALLY STEPPED RIGHT
INTO THE PAIL, RIGHT UP TO MY
KNEE, AND I ENDED UP GETTING
TOTALLY SOAKED.
>> [GIRLS GIGGLING]
>> I COULD HAVE KILLED DAD
FOR LEAVING IT THERE.
WHAT A LAMEBRAIN HE
IS SOMETIMES.
>> SOUNDS LIKE MY DAD.
LUCKY YOU DIDN'T
TWIST YOUR ANKLE.
>> ACTUALLY, I TOLD HIM
I DID TWIST IT.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN HOW WHITE
HE TURNED.
>> [GIRLS GIGGLING]
>> SOTA.
>> HUH?
>> [SIGHS]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH
YOU, SOTA?
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR APPETITE?
>> UH--NOTHING'S THE MATTER, MA.
>> HMM.
MAYBE THIS WILL HELP YOU,
MY BOY.
>> WHAT'S THAT THING?
>> A MERMAID SCALE THAT'S BEEN
PASSED DOWN FOR GENERATIONS.
TAPE THIS SCALE TO YOUR NAVEL
WHEN YOU GO TO BED, AND YOU'LL
BE CURED.
>> BUYO.
>> [MEOW]
>> YOU HAVE IT.
>> AAH!
NO, NO, NO, WAIT!
GET BACK HERE!
GIVE ME THAT...
>> MAY I BE EXCUSED?
>> DON'T EAT IT!
IT'S A FAMILY HEIRLOOM!
>> I WONDER WHAT'S GOTTEN
INTO HIM.
>> SOMETHING TELLS ME HE'S NOT
FEELING WELL.
>> OH, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
>> HUH?
>> TECHNICALLY, I GUESS
HE IS SICK.
LOVESICK, TO BE EXACT.
>> HE'S LOVESICK?
>> WONDERFUL.
I'LL MAKE RED BEAN RICE
TO CELEBRATE.
>> EXCELLENT.
I'LL USE THAT REASON
FOR KAGOME'S NEXT ABSENCE.
>> NO, YOU WON'T!
>> IT WILL FOOL YOUR TEACHER.
>> IT WILL NOT!
>> WHAT A WONDERFUL SICKNESS
TO HAVE.
>> [YAWNS]
>> SAY, INUYASHA?
>> HMM?
WHAT IS IT?
>> CAN I, UH, TALK TO YOU?
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> IT'S KIND OF A
MAN-TO-MAN THING.
>> UH...
[DOG BARKING]
>> HMPH.
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TALK,
THEN I'M GOING.
>> NO.
HANG ON.
>> WHAT IS IT?
HURRY UP AND TALK IF YOU GOTTA.
>> WHAT IS LOVE?
>> HUH?
>> IS LOVE ETERNAL?
>> UHH!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHERE IS THIS COMING FROM?
>> TELL ME.
WHO SAID "I LOVE YOU" FIRST?
WAS IT YOU OR KAGOME?
>> HUH?
>> SO, WHO WAS IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT ARE YOU ASKING FOR?
>> WELL, YOU ARE BOYFRIEND
AND GIRLFRIEND, AREN'T YOU?
>> HUH?
>> AREN'T YOU?
WELL, IF YOU WEREN'T HER
BOYFRIEND, KAGOME WOULDN'T SKIP
SO MUCH SCHOOL TO GO SEE YOU
IN YOUR ERA, AND YOU WOULDN'T
COME HERE TO TAKE CARE OF HER
WHEN SHE'S SICK.
>> HUH--UHH--UHH?
>> SO, WHO SAID IT FIRST?
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO HER?
>> GET OFF MY BACK!
AS IF I'D SAY MUSHY STUFF
LIKE THAT TO KAGOME.
>> YOU MEAN KAGOME
TOLD YOU FIRST?
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
>> HUH--UHH-UHH--
>> COME ON.
DON'T TELL ME NEITHER OF YOU
HAVE SAID ANYTHING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> SO YOU HAVEN'T.
>> AAH!
YOU--YOU--YOU--YOU!
>> SAY, INUYASHA...
>> HUH?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD DO?
>> [THINKING] HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
>> THE GIRL I'M TALKING ABOUT
IS CALLED HITOMI.
>> [THINKING] I DIDN'T ASK YOU.
>> SHE GOES TO MY SCHOOL.
WE'RE EVEN IN THE SAME CLASS,
AND SHE SITS RIGHT NEXT TO ME
IN THE CLASSROOM.
>> [GIGGLING]
>> OH, SHE'S ONE OF THE CUTEST
GIRLS I'VE EVER SEEN, WITH
GREAT BIG EYES, HER SKIN SO
NICE, SHE USED TO LIVE OVERSEAS,
SHE DOESN'T LIKE PARSLEY,
AND SHE NEVER CARRIES
A BACKPACK.
>> I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND HALF OF
THAT, BUT BASICALLY, YOU'RE
TELLING ME YOU LOVE THIS HITOMI
GIRL, RIGHT?
>> UH--HMM.
YEAH.
BUT I DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
IF HITOMI FEELS THE SAME WAY.
>> HMM.
>> SO I FIGURED I SHOULD JUST
COME OUT AND TELL HER
HOW I FEEL!
>> [THINKING] AND YOU'RE
TELLING ME ALL OF THIS BECAUSE?
>> YOU GOT TO HELP ME.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
>> LET ME PRACTICE ON YOU.
>> HUH?
>> LET ME PRACTICE SAYING
"I LOVE YOU" SO I CAN
TELL HITOMI.
>> EH-HEH!
>> PLEASE SAY YES,
>> EEEH!
>> [SIGHS] ALL RIGHT,
BUT JUST ONCE.
>> OH, MAN, THIS IS GREAT.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HURRY IT UP!
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'M
READY FOR THIS.
>> IF YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
SAY IT, THEN I'M GOING IN.
>> NO, D-DON'T LEAVE ME!
>> [BOTH GRUNTING]
>> [GRUMBLING]
>> MMM.
I...
L...
LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU!
>> AM I INTERRUPTING?
>> HUH?
>> UHH--UHH-UHH!
>> [INUYASHA AND SOTA GROANING]
>> [LAUGHING]
>> COME ON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LAUGH.
>> LIGHTEN UP.
IT'S SO STUPID IT'S FUNNY.
YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY SHOULD'VE
COME AND ASKED ME FOR ADVICE.
>> HUH?
>> I'M PRETTY CONFIDENT I KNOW
A LOT MORE ABOUT A GIRL'S
FEELINGS THAN INUYASHA.
>> WELL, OF COURSE YOU KNOW
MORE THAN ME.
YOU'RE A GIRL.
>> I'M GOING TO HELP YOU.
YOU'RE MY FAVORITE LITTLE
BROTHER, AND I'M GONNA
SHOW YOU THE ROPES.
>> UH.
HMM.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> IT'S PERFECT.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO GREAT
LOOKING LIKE THIS.
HERE.
>> COME ON, SIS.
>> NOW, LISTEN.
DURING LUNCH BREAK, JUST
GIVE HER A HINT ABOUT
HOW YOU FEEL.
THEN AFTER CLASS, CALL HITOMI
OUT, AND WHEN YOU'RE ALL ALONE,
JUST BLURT IT RIGHT OUT!
>> YOU MEAN I GOTTA WEAR THIS
OUTFIT TILL AFTER SCHOOL?
>> WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
THIS IS A LIFE-CHANGING MOMENT,
SO BUCK UP!
>> YEAH, BUT--
>> OFF YOU GO.
DO YOUR BEST, NOW.
>> UHH.
>> YOU CAN DO IT, SOTA.
BANZAI!
COME ON, INUYASHA, JOIN IN.
>> [GROANS] BANZAI!
>> BANZAI!
BANZAI!
>> IN LOVE?
>> YUP, HEAD OVER HEELS.
>> KAGOME, DID HOJO COME OUT
AND TELL YOU HE LOVES YOU?
>> HE MUST HAVE, AND THAT'S
WHY YOU LOOK SO HAPPY.
>> SO YOU'LL BE TWO-TIMING HIM.
>> MM-HMM.
>> NO, YOU GUYS.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT HOJO.
>> BUT THEN WHO?
YOU MEAN, ALL THAT TIME THAT
OTHER GUY HADN'T TOLD YOU
HE LOVED YOU?
>> I'D GET THINGS STRAIGHT IF
I WERE YOU, OTHERWISE THERE WILL
BE NOTHING BUT TROUBLE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT I'M
SAYING HERE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT SOTA, NOT ME.
>> SOTA?
>> WHAT?
YOU MEAN YOUR KID BROTHER?
>> THAT'S THE ONE.
HE'S GOING TO TELL A GIRL IN
SCHOOL THAT HE LOVES HER!
I WONDER HOW HE'LL MAKE OUT.
>> SHE SEEMS EXCITED, ESPECIALLY
CONSIDERING IT'S SOMEONE ELSE.
>> I'LL SAY.
THIS IS ONE SIDE OF KAGOME
WE HAVEN'T SEEN BEFORE.
>> [GOBBLING]
>> SOTA'S TAKING A LONG TIME.
WAS HE TURNED AWAY?
I DOUBT IT, BUT ANYTHING CAN
HAPPEN ON THE PLAYING FIELD
OF LOVE.
>> I BET THERE WAS A FLAW
IN YOUR LITTLE PLAN.
>> HUH?
[BANGING]
>> I'M HOME.
>> [GASPS]
>> HUH?
[BANGING]
>> HMM.
>> SOTA.
SOTA, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> [MOANS]
>> I'D KNOW THAT HOPELESS
LOOK ANYWHERE.
THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
SHE SENT HIM PACKING.
[THUNDER]
UHH.
COME ON, SOTA.
IT'S REALLY NOT THAT BAD.
>> HUH.
CHEER UP, GLOOMY BOY.
THERE'S LOTS AND LOTS OF
OTHER WOMEN OUT THERE.
>> HEY, DON'T SAY THAT!
>> WHY?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
>> IT'S NOT THAT.
>> HUH?
>> SHE DIDN'T REALLY
TURN ME DOWN.
>> WELL, THEN, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I COULDN'T TELL HER.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> I CALLED HITOMI OUT AFTER
SCHOOL, JUST LIKE YOU
TOLD ME TO.
>> WHAT DID YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT, SOTA?
>> WELL, UH, I...
>> IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
SAY, I'M GOING HOME.
>> UH--JUST A MINUTE, HITOMI.
>> HUH?
>> UH--I...
>> UH--
>> I...
I--I...
OHH.
I...
MMF.
>> SOTA?
>> UHH.
>> YOU KNOW, I DON'T REALLY
LIKE BOYS WHO CAN'T JUST
COME OUT AND SAY WHAT THEY
WANT TO SAY.
HMPH.
>> [GROANING]
[SOBBING] OH, I'M NEVER
FALLING IN LOVE AGAIN!
>> SO THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
>> STUPID, YOU HAVEN'T EVEN
TOLD HER YET, SO QUIT CRYING
LIKE A BABY.
>> WHAT'S THE POINT OF
TELLING HER NOW?
I'M A WEAKLING, AND SHE'S
TOO GOOD FOR ME.
I CAN'T EVEN SAY WHAT I WANT TO!
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL,
THEN CHANGE YOURSELF!
>> UH--
>> DON'T WORRY, KID.
I'LL TOUGHEN YOU UP
AND MAKE A MAN OUT OF YOU.
>> INUYASHA.
>> IRON REAVER, SOUL STEALER!
>> HUH...
>> HMPH.
OK, NOW YOU TRY IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> TRY IT.
>> UHH.
IRON REAVER, SOUL STEALER.
>> EXCELLENT.
THAT'S NOT BAD AT ALL
FOR YOUR FIRST TIME.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
>> OK, GIVE IT ANOTHER SHOT.
>> OK.
IRON REAVER, SOUL STEALER.
>> COME ON, INUYASHA.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> IRON REAVER, SOUL STEALER.
>> WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU
TRYING TO DO?
>> THIS IS ALL A
MATTER OF SPIRIT.
I'M JUST TRYING TO GET HIS
ADRENALINE PUMPING AND GIVE HIM
SOME CONFIDENCE.
>> OH, I SEE.
>> HE'S IN GOOD HANDS.
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> UHH.
>> OH, JUST TALKING.
YOU KNOW, SOTA, I MIGHT BE
IMAGINING IT, BUT THAT
TRAINING SEEMS TO BE
MAKING YOU STRONGER.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.
I THINK YOU HAVE GOTTEN
A BIT STRONGER.
>> YOU REALLY THINK SO?
>> IT'S TOTALLY OBVIOUS.
YOU'RE LIKE A WHOLE NEW PERSON.
>> YOU SEE, SOTA?
>> DO YOUR BEST!
>> [MOANS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
>> BANZAI!
BANZAI!
BANZAI!...
>> NOW GRANDPA AND MOM
ARE IN ON IT.
>> NEVER MIND THEM, SOTA.
JUST GET OUT THERE
AND DO YOUR BEST!
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING TELLS ME
THIS IS A TRICK.
>> BANZAI!
BANZAI!
>> OH, MAN!
THIS STUFF IS WAY HARDER THAN
SLAYING DEMONS.
>> I SURE HOPE IT WORKS.
>> HMPH.
YOUR KID BROTHER SURE IS
HARD TO PERSUADE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
WE'RE RELATED SOMETIMES.
>> JUST MULLING OVER THE PROBLEM
LIKE THAT ISN'T GOING TO
SOLVE ANYTHING AT ALL.
>> I'LL SAY.
IF HE LOVES HER, HE SHOULD
JUST COME OUT AND SAY SO.
>> YEAH, DEFINITELY!
>> HUH?
>> SOTA.
>> SO, YOU CAME BACK WITH YOUR
TAIL BETWEEN YOUR LEGS.
>> I CAN'T DO THIS.
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT, AND THEN I
REALIZED THAT A LITTLE TRAINING
ISN'T GOING TO MAKE ME STRONG.
I CAN'T CHANGE MY PERSONALITY
THAT EASILY!
>> OOPS.
HE FIGURED IT OUT.
>> AWW, DAMN IT ALL!
WOULD YOU CUT THIS OUT?
STOP DAWDLING LIKE THIS AND
GO AND TELL THE GIRL
HOW YOU FEEL ALREADY!
>> YEAH, IT'S EASIER SAID
THAN DONE.
>> QUIT MAKING EXCUSES.
COME HERE!
>> HEY!
STOP!
>> HANG ON.
WAIT, INUYASHA.
>> UHH!
>> OFF YOU GO, AND DON'T YOU
COME BACK UNTIL YOU'VE TOLD HER.
YOU GOT THAT?
>> YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
>> IF YOU DO COME BACK BEFORE
YOU'VE TOLD HER, THEN YOU'RE NOT
GETTING BACK INSIDE.
>> BUT THIS IS MY HOUSE.
>> COME ON!
HAVE A LITTLE BACKBONE!
MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
THAT'S ALL IT TAKES.
>> I KNOW, BUT--
>> BUT NOTHING.
DON'T BE SO WISHY-WASHY, SOTA.
DIDN'T YOU TELL ME THE OTHER
NIGHT THAT YOU LOVED THIS GIRL?
>> UHH.
>> LISTEN, ARE YOU A MAN
OR AREN'T YOU?
HAVE COURAGE AND JUST GO FOR IT!
>> [SIGHS]
>> HMPH.
>> CROSS YOUR FINGERS?
>> SURE.
>> GOOD LUCK, SOTA.
>> HMM.
>> LET'S GO, INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> I'M HIS BIG SISTER.
I GOT TO WATCH OUT FOR HIM.
>> WHAT?
YOU MEAN LIKE SPY?
>> CALL IT WHAT YOU WANT.
>> HEY, KAGOME!
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU SEEM SORT OF DIFFERENT
TODAY, SOTA.
>> HITOMI?
>> HUH?
>> I HAVE SOMETHING IMPORTANT
TO SAY.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> [MOANS]
>> [GRUMBLES]
>> [INUYASHA'S VOICE] LISTEN,
ARE YOU A MAN OR AREN'T YOU?
HAVE COURAGE AND JUST GO FOR IT!
>> [THINKING] INUYASHA.
HITOMI, I'M NOT STRONG,
AND I'M NOT VERY RELIABLE,
AND PROBABLY NOT VERY GOOD AT
SAYING HOW I FEEL, BUT--WELL--
I REALLY, REALLY LIKE YOU,
HITOMI.
>> SOTA.
>> WOULD YOU BE MY GIRLFRIEND?
>> [GRUMBLING]
>> OK.
>> [GASPS] YOU WILL?
>> HMM.
>> SOTA.
>> HUH?
>> THIRD-GRADERS SURE GROW UP
FAST THESE DAYS.
>> GOT TO, UH, GIVE THEM CREDIT.
HEH.
>> HEH.
>> OH.
AAH!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
>> 1, 2, 3.
I THINK WE'VE GOT IT ALL.
>> WELL, THEN, I GUESS
IT'S TIME.
>> YEP.
>> SEE YOU LATER, SOTA.
>> OK.
GOOD LUCK OVER THERE.
>> BYE.
>> [GRUNTS]
>> UH, INUYASHA?
>> YEAH?
>> THANK YOU.
>> HMM.
SURE.
LET'S GO, KAGOME.
>> YOU BET!
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR, SHIPPO?
>> KURORO, A CAT DEMON THAT
USED TO LIVE IN KOUME'S VILLAGE.
A STRANGE PRIEST HAD HER
BANISHED, SAYING SHE BROUGHT
BAD LUCK.
KURORO LOOKS A LOT LIKE
KIRARA, AND SHE'S VERY SMART.
>> CATS ARE NATURAL ENEMIES
OF RATS.
I BET THIS HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE VILLAGE BEING OVERRUN
BY HUGE PACKS OF RATS!
NEXT TIME, THE SUSPICIOUS FAITH
HEALER AND THE BLACK KIRARA.
>> I CAN TAKE CARE OF
THIS PROBLEM!