- POSSESSION OF THE SACRED
SHIKON JEWEL
BESTOWS TREMENDOUS POWER
UPON DEMONS
AND OTHERS WITH EVIL
RESIDING IN THEIR HEARTS.
MY SISTER, KIKYO,
HAD DIED TRYING TO SEAL
THE JEWEL'S POWERS.
HOWEVER, SHE WAS REINCARNATED
AS A YOUNG WOMAN NAMED KAGOME,
AND RETURNED TO COMPLETE
HER MISSION.
NOW THE JOURNEY BEGINS
FOR INUYASHA,
A HALF-DEMON
WITH A HUMAN MOTHER,
AND THE YOUNG WOMAN
FROM THE MODERN AGE.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- HMM.
CLEAR.
HERE GOES.
- WHAT'S YOUR HURRY, KAGOME?
UHH.
- ERK!
- NOT SO FAST.
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE
UNTIL YOU HAND OVER THE SHARDS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
- IN MY ERA, GIRLS GO TO SCHOOL,
AND IT JUST SO HAPPENS
THAT THIS GIRL
HAS A HUGE FINAL TOMORROW
TO STUDY FOR!
MY ATTENDANCE IS SO BAD,
I MIGHT FAIL THE CLASS,
EVEN IF I ACE THE EXAM.
HEY! NOW WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[GRUNTING]
- WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE?
I'M GOING TO COVER UP THE WELL
FOR GOOD.
THEN YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO ESCAPE
TO THAT STRANGE ERA OF YOURS.
GOOD RIDDANCE!
- SIT!
- HUH?
- SIT! SIT! SIT!
SIT! SIT! SIT! SIT!
- UHH! UHH! AUGH!
UHH! AUGH!
UHH. UHH.
- STAY, BOY.
I'LL BE BACK IN 3 DAYS,
AND DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT FOLLOWING ME!
UHH.
- [CHANTING IN JAPANESE]
- WHY WASTE YOUR TIME WITH THAT
CHANTING STUFF, GRANDPA?
IT DOESN'T ACTUALLY WORK,
DOES IT?
- IT DOES.
THIS ANCIENT
GET-OUT-OF-THE-WELL CHANT
HAS BEEN PASSED DOWN
THROUGH GENERATIONS
OF HIGURASHI PRIESTS.
[LAUGHS]
- THEN HOW COME YOU'VE BEEN
AT IT FOR 3 DAYS AND NIGHTS
AND KAGOME STILL HASN'T
COME BACK?
- HMM.
- AND TOUCHDOWN.
WHOA!
- NOW FOR THE SECRET RICE WINE.
UHH.
- HMM?
UHH!
WHAT IS THIS STUFF?
IT SMELLS LIKE SAKE.
- KAGOME!
IT'S YOU!
I KNEW MY PRAYERS
WOULD BE ANSWERED.
- THANKS FOR WORRYING
ABOUT ME, GRAMPS.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH
IT MEANS TO ME.
[AHCHOO]
- SEE, SOTA?
I TOLD YOU IT WOULD WORK.
- HEY, SHE'S BACK!
YOU REALLY DID IT, GRAMPS!
- NO TIME LIKE THE PRESENT
TO SHAVE YOUR HEAD
AND START TRAINING
FOR THE PRIESTHOOD.
- SHAVE MY HEAD?
- OF COURSE.
TIME TO PASS THE TORCH.
- GET REAL.
I'M GOING TO BE
A FAMOUS SOCCER PLAYER.
- SOCCER? WHAT KIND OF A JOB
IS THAT?
DUSTING ANTIQUES AND CHECKING
FOR POCKET CHANGE, THAT--
- VERY INTERESTING, BUT COULD WE
FINISH THIS CONVERSATION
AFTER YOU'VE HELPED ME
OUT OF THE WELL?
- ANYWAY, MOM WANTS ME
TO BE A DOCTOR.
- A DOCTOR?
WELL, I SUPPOSE YOU COULD BE
A DOCTOR ON THE WEEKENDS,
BUT WE'RE STILL GOING
TO START YOU TRAINING
FOR THE PRIESTHOOD TODAY.
[AHCHOO]
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM, BUYO?
GOT A COLD OR SOMETHING?
OR MAYBE MY HAIR STILL SMELLS
A LITTLE GROSS.
- [WHIMPERING]
- HERE'S YOUR NEW
SCHOOL UNIFORM, KAGOME.
I'LL PUT IT IN YOUR ROOM
FOR YOU.
- THANKS, MOM.
LOOKS GOOD.
- WHERE'S THAT DOG GUY INUYASHA?
DIDN'T YOU BRING HIM HOME
WITH YOU?
- OF COURSE I DIDN'T.
I'VE GOT BETTER THINGS TO DO
THAN SPEND MY TIME
BABY-SITTING A DEMON ALL DAY.
HA!
OH, BROTHER.
MY LIFE'S GETTING A BIT
TOO COMPLICATED.
I'VE LIVED HERE
AT HIGURASHI SHRINE
SINCE I WAS 4.
THERE'S GRAMPS, MOM,
MY LITTLE BROTHER SOTA,
AND ME, YOUR AVERAGE
MIDDLE SCHOOL GIRL.
BUT THAT'S WHERE THINGS
START GETTING WEIRD.
WE HAVE A HIDDEN WELL
ON THE GROUNDS
THAT LEADS TO THE FEUDAL ERA,
NOT TO MENTION
ALL KINDS OF MONSTERS
THAT ARE AFTER THE SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
NOW, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
MY LIFE IS ANYTHING BUT AVERAGE.
I KEEP THINKING
I'M GOING TO WAKE UP
TO FIND OUT IT'S ALL
A BAD DREAM OR SOMETHING,
BUT IT'S NOT A DREAM.
IT'S VERY REAL,
AND I'LL JUST HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO DEAL WITH IT.
[SIGH]
RIGHT!
[LAUGHTER]
- HEY, WAIT UP, GUYS!
[GASPS]
- KAGOME!
YOU SURE YOU'RE FEELING
WELL ENOUGH TO BE AT SCHOOL?
- HEH HEH.
- WE HEARD ABOUT YOUR ACCIDENT
WITH THE CAT.
THAT IS ONE NASTY PLACE
TO GET BITTEN.
HOW'S YOUR BACK
AFTER THAT FALL OUT OF BED?
- BEFORE YOU PUT YOUR BACK OUT,
YOU WERE AWAY FOR SOME
LYME DISEASE TESTS.
- GOT THE RESULTS BACK YET?
- AND WHAT ABOUT
THAT CASE OF RINGWORM?
[GROANS]
- COME ON, GRAMPS.
COULDN'T YOU HAVE TOLD THEM
I HAVE A COLD?
- HEY, KAGOME.
- HUH?
- HOW ARE YOU MAKING OUT
WITH THOSE BUNIONS?
- HUH?
[GASPS]
- IT'S HOJO, THE MEGA-HUNK.
- WOW, TALK ABOUT
A DOUBLE WHAMMY.
BUNIONS AND GOUT?
- OHH!
- HERE, THIS IS FROM THE SHOP.
YOU KNOW, FOR YOUR AILMENTS.
MOM WRAPPED IT UP.
I HOPE YOU LIKE PINK.
[GASPS]
- UH...HUH?
- THERAPEUTIC SANDALS
FOR YOUR BUNIONS.
- OHH!
- KAGOME!
ARE YOU GOING OUT WITH HOJO?
- 'COURSE NOT.
I HAVEN'T GOT THE TIME.
DOES THAT GUY TOTALLY HAVE
THE HOTS FOR YOU, OR WHAT?
- OH, YEAH.
- YOU MEAN, HE'S NEVER EVEN
TALKED TO YOU BEFORE?
- NOT REALLY.
- AREN'T YOU EVEN EXCITED?
- OH, NO.
MAYBE SHE LIKES SOMEONE ELSE.
- COME ON.
I DON'T LIKE ANYONE.
- IF YOU DID,
WHAT WOULD HE BE LIKE?
THE ATHLETIC TYPE
OR THE INTELLECTUAL TYPE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- HUH?
- HE DEFINITELY WOULDN'T
BE AGGRESSIVE,
AND NOT SELFISH.
HE WOULDN'T GET MAD EASILY.
HE'D BE KIND AND UNDERSTANDING,
AND HE'D BRING ME FLOWERS
AND WRITE ME POETRY.
SOMEONE THE EXACT OPPOSITE
OF INUYASHA.
THAT'S THE PERFECT GUY FOR ME.
- I'LL TAKE THAT
AS AN UNDECIDED.
- MAYBE SHE IS STILL SICK.
[HUMMING]
- UH, UH...OHH!
- STOP LAZING ABOUT.
GET OFF YE DUFF AND SEEK OUT
SOME INFORMATION
ON THE SACRED JEWEL.
- AND IF YE HADN'T NOTICED,
MY BACK'S OUT OF COMMISSION,
THANKS TO ALL THOSE
"SIT" COMMANDS.
OOH, YOU JUST WAIT TILL
YOU COME BACK, KAGOME.
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THIS!
OW! OOH!
- HUH?
SOMETHING'S SMOKING.
THE STOREHOUSE IS ON FIRE!
THIS IS TERRIBLE!
THE NOH MASK HAS BURNED
THROUGH THE TALISMANS
THAT HAVE SEALED UP ITS EVIL
FOR GENERATIONS.
- I MUST HAVE A PHYSICAL BODY.
- UHH!
MY GREAT-GREAT-GREAT-GREAT
GRANDFATHER
EXORCISED THAT EVIL MASK
FOR A NOH ACTOR
WHO BROUGHT IT TO HIM.
IT WAS CALLED
THE FLESH-EATING MASK,
AND WAS RUMORED TO HAVE
INCREDIBLE MALEVOLENT POWERS.
I MUST DO EVERYTHING POSSIBLE
TO SEAL IT UP AGAIN!
UHH...AHH!
A BODY.
I MUST POSSESS A BODY.
- AAH!
UHH.
AAH!
- A BODY.
I MUST POSSESS A HUMAN BODY.
- HE'S LOOKING FOR LIVING FLESH
TO EMBODY AND WREAK HAVOC ON US!
AAH!
- MY SOUL YEARNS
FOR A LIVING BODY.
- I MUST STOP IT.
- GIVE ME FLESH AND BLOOD!
[RINGING]
[SIREN WAILING]
- HEY, DID YOU HEAR?
HIGURASHI SHRINE'S ON FIRE.
- COOL! LET'S CHECK IT OUT!
- YEAH!
- HUH?
- NO PUSHING, PLEASE.
- YUP, 3 UNITS.
- IT'S JUST A SMALL FIRE, FOLKS.
STAY BEHIND THE...
- LET ME THROUGH.
I'VE GOT TO GET IN!
- HEY, YOU!
THIS AREA'S OFF LIMITS!
- THANK YOU FOR
ALL YOUR HELP, OFFICER.
- NO PROBLEM.
- MOM!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- KAGOME!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
WHERE'S THE FIRE?
- THE OLD STOREHOUSE
CAUGHT ON FIRE
AND GRANDPA WAS TRAPPED INSIDE
IN THE SMOKE.
- GRANDPA'S HURT?
- OH, DON'T WORRY.
HE'D FAINTED AND SUFFERED FROM
A BIT OF SMOKE INHALATION,
BUT THEY SAY 2 OR 3 DAYS
IN THE HOSPITAL
AND HE SHOULD BE GOOD AS NEW.
I'M JUST ON MY WAY
TO CHECK IN ON HIM
AND SEE HOW HE'S DOING.
- I'M GOING WITH YOU.
- KAGOME, YOU STAY HERE
AND WAIT FOR SOTA.
SOMEONE'S GOT TO EXPLAIN
THINGS TO HIM.
- YEAH, OK.
HOW COULD A FIRE START
IN THE STOREHOUSE?
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS
DOESN'T SOUND RIGHT.
- [SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
- OK. YEAH, YEAH.
THERE'S SOME DAMAGE...
- HUH?
WHAT'S DOWN THERE?
WHOA--
[MUFFLED SPEECH]
- HEY, WH-WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- [MUFFLED SPEECH]
- SAY SOMETHING!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- KAGOME!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- DON'T WORRY, SOTA.
IT WASN'T IN THE MAIN SHRINE,
AND NO ONE WAS SERIOUSLY HURT.
[CRASH]
- HUH?
- STOP THE TRUCK!
- HUH--HUH--UHH!
- THAT WAY!
HURRY!
- SIR, REQUESTING A CALL IN
FOR BACKUP.
- THIS JUST IN.
A FIRE TRUCK IS DRIVING WILDLY
THROUGH THE STREETS,
COMPLETELY OUT OF CONTROL
AND SMASHING INTO
ANYTHING AND ANYONE IN ITS PATH.
THE NUMBER OF INJURED SO FAR
HAS NOT BEEN CONFIRMED,
SINCE EVERY PERSON
THAT CROSSES ITS PATH
SEEMS TO HAVE VANISHED
INTO THIN AIR.
THAT'S ALL THE INFORMATION
WE HAVE AT PRESENT,
BUT UNTIL MORE IS KNOWN
ABOUT THE INCIDENT,
WE STRONGLY ADVISE EVERYONE
TO STAY OFF THE STREETS.
- THE FLESH IS DISINTEGRATING.
IF I CAN FIND MORE SHARDS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL,
I CAN GAIN THE POWER TO STOP
THIS FLESH FROM DECOMPOSING.
THEN I WILL HAVE AN ALMIGHTY
EVERLASTING BODY
OF LIVING, PULSATING FLESH.
- HOW'S GRANDPA?
IS HE AWAKE YET?
- HE'S STILL UNCONSCIOUS,
BUT THE DOCTOR'S
A LITTLE BAFFLED.
HE SAYS IT'S NOTHING SERIOUS,
SO HE EXPECTED GRANDPA TO HAVE
WOKEN UP BY NOW.
- OH...
- I'M SURE IT'S
JUST A MATTER OF TIME.
LET'S NOT FORGET HIS AGE
IS A FACTOR.
- HUH?
WHAT ARE THOSE?
LET ME SEE.
- THESE? THEY'RE TALISMANS.
THE FIREFIGHTERS FOUND THEM
PLASTERED OVER GRANDPA'S FACE
AND IN HIS MOUTH.
POOR GRANDPA.
SOMETHING MUST HAVE
REALLY SPOOKED HIM.
[MOANING]
- HUH?
- BEWARE THE FLESH-EATING MASK.
BEWARE THE ANCIENT
FLESH-EATING MASK.
- SO IT'S JUST
THE TWO OF US HERE TONIGHT,
SINCE MOM'S GOING
TO STAY AT THE HOSPITAL
AND WATCH OVER GRANDPA
IN CASE HE WAKES UP.
[GRUNTING]
HMM?
- SIS, GOT ANY ROOM
FOR BUYO AND ME TO SLEEP HERE?
- NO CHANCE.
YOU CAN STAY IN YOUR OWN ROOM.
- PLEASE, SIS?
- DON'T BE SUCH A SCAREDY-CAT.
I'M GOING TO BE UP ALL NIGHT
STUDYING FOR A TEST.
THE ONLY THING YOU SHOULD
BE SCARED OF
ARE THE DUST BUNNIES
UNDER YOUR BED.
- WHEN GRANDPA WAS SCARED,
HE COVERED HIS FACE
IN THOSE WRITTEN SPELLS.
SOMETHING CREEPY
HAPPENED IN THERE, SIS.
I JUST KNOW IT.
- HMM?
- BEWARE THE FLESH-EATING MASK.
- GUH--
- SOMETHING'S WRONG.
WE'VE NEVER HAD TROUBLE
LIKE THIS
AT THE SHRINE BEFORE,
SO WHY NOW?
WHY, AFTER
ALL THESE GENERATIONS?
- HUH?
THE JEWEL SHARDS!
THAT'S IT!
IT'S BECAUSE I BROUGHT
THE JEWEL SHARDS BACK!
[SIREN WAILING]
HUH?
[WHISTLES]
ALL RIGHT, HERE IT COMES.
- THIS IS IT, BOYS.
EVERYONE AT THE READY.
GET READY.
- [PEOPLE SPEAKING AT ONCE]
- STEP OUT OF THE VEHICLE.
- GET HIM OUT OF THERE.
[SHOUTING]
- OH, NO!
NO!
WE'VE GOT TO GO HOME!
- [SHOUTING]
- IT'S TAKING OVER!
- UH--UHH!
- WHAT IS THAT?
OH, MY--
[SHOUTING]
- BEWARE OF THE FLESH-EATING
NOH MASK.
BEWARE OF THE NOH MASK!
[SCREAMING]
- UHH!
[GLASS CLINKS]
A NOH MASK?
THAT MUST BE
THE FLESH-EATING MASK
THAT GRANDPA WAS MUMBLING ABOUT
IN THE HOSPITAL.
AAH!
- JEWEL.
I MUST HAVE THE SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
- UH...UHH.
- GIVE ME THE PIECES
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL!
- COME ON, SOTA.
THIS IS NO TIME
TO ZONE OUT ON ME.
WE'VE GOT TO GET AWAY
FROM THE MASK.
I HAVE TO CALL INUYASHA,
'CAUSE HE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN HELP US.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- KAGOME...
LOOK AT YOUR FINGERS.
YOUR FINGERS ARE BLEEDING.
- FORGET IT.
I CUT MYSELF ON THE GLASS,
THAT'S ALL.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
HUH?
- HUH?
[SCREAMING]
- THE JEWEL SHARDS.
GIVE ME THE JEWEL SHARDS!
- THE MASK HAS A JEWEL FRAGMENT
ON ITS FOREHEAD,
SO THAT'S WHY IT'S
AFTER THESE SHARDS.
I'VE GOT TO GET SOTA
AWAY FROM HERE
AND OUT OF DANGER!
SOTA! RUN TO THE HIDDEN WELL
AND GET INUYASHA.
TELL HIM THERE ARE
MORE JEWEL SHARDS HERE.
THAT SHOULD BE ENOUGH TO GET HIM
TO CROSS OVER AND HELP US.
- I HAVE TO GO
IN THAT SPOOKY WELL?
- YOU CAN HANDLE IT.
JUST GET GOING!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GULP]
- I CAN HANDLE THIS.
YAAA!
[CRASH]
- BLAH! OOH.
HOW COME I'M STILL HERE?
- WAH!
WHAT WENT WRONG?
- [MEOWING]
- I'VE GOT TO GET
THROUGH THE WELL,
'CAUSE SIS IS IN TROUBLE.
THE MASK IS AFTER HER,
AND I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN HELP.
[SOBBING]
H-HUH?
IT'S YOU.
YOU'RE INUYASHA.
- IN THE FLESH, KID.
NOW WHAT'S THIS PROBLEM
YOU NEED HELP WITH?
UHH. UHH.
UHH.
HANG ON TIGHT, KID.
IT'S A LONG WAY DOWN.
- I GUESS I WASN'T STRONG ENOUGH
TO PASS THROUGH THE HIDDEN WELL.
- LUCKY FOR YOU,
BECAUSE IN MY WORLD,
THERE ARE PLENTY OF MONSTERS
WHO'D JUST LOVE
TO HAVE YOU FOR LUNCH.
- GUH--
- UHH.
UHH.
- DO YOU KNOW
WHERE TO FIND MY SISTER?
- SURE.
I'M NOT HUMAN, REMEMBER?
I CAN PICK UP SCENTS
FROM MILES AROUND
WITH THIS NOSE.
- KAGOME CUT HER HAND
ON SOME GLASS.
- DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME THAT.
I CAN SMELL THE BLOOD
FROM BACK IN THE WELL.
FEAR NOT.
I'LL RESCUE KAGOME
BEFORE SHE GETS INTO
ANY REAL TROUBLE.
- I'LL TELL YOU WHAT HE'S LIKE.
HE'S WHINY AND A SHOW-OFF
AND A TOTAL EGOMANIAC.
[SIGH]
THE GUY'S A COMPLETE PAIN.
- THIS CAN'T BE THE SAME GUY
KAGOME WAS TELLING ME ABOUT.
SURE, HIS OUTFIT'S
A BIT OUT OF DATE,
BUT INUYASHA'S
THE ONLY GUY AROUND HERE
I THINK I CAN TRUST.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- INUYASHA'S NOT HERE YET.
WHAT'S TAKING HIM SO LONG?
AAH!
OH, NO!
- I NEED THE SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL!
- IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
- NICE TIMING.
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- SURE. I'M FINE.
- OH, SIS.
- HEY, WHAT'S WITH
ALL THE TEARS?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WEREN'T AFRAID.
- IT'S OK.
INUYASHA'S GONNA DESTROY
THAT MONSTER FOR US,
AND IT'LL ALL BE OVER.
- AHEM.
- HUH?
- BEFORE WE GET ON
WITH MY LITTLE
RESCUE MISSION HERE,
THIS MIGHT BE AN APPROPRIATE
TIME FOR AN APOLOGY,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
- HUH?
APOLOGY FOR WHAT?
SIT!
- FOR WHAT?
FOR SHOUTING
ALL THOSE INCANTATIONS
AND PUTTING MY BACK OUT,
THAT'S WHAT.
YEAH, SHE HAS THE GALL
TO BEG ME FOR HELP.
- OH, THAT.
YEAH, NOW IT'S COMING BACK.
OK. I'M VERY SORRY.
THERE. YOU SATISFIED NOW?
- SHE MAKES IT SOUND LIKE
SHE'S APOLOGIZING FOR
STEPPING ON MY FOOT.
MAYBE I'LL GO BACK.
- YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE US HERE.
BESIDES, THE MASK HAS A SHARD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
DON'T YOU WANT TO ADD IT
TO OUR COLLECTION?
- HMPH.
- HMPH!
- SO HE'S REFUSING TO SAVE US
OVER A LITTLE APOLOGY?
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY HERO?
HE'S SHRINKING
TO LIFE-SIZE PROPORTIONS
BEFORE MY VERY EYES.
- OH, NO.
THE MASK!
- WHO DARES TO ATTACK ME?
- INUYASHA, AIM FOR THE MASK.
THE SHARD IS IN THE FOREHEAD!
- I AM THE FLESH-EATING MASK.
CENTURIES AGO, I WAS CARVED
FROM A GIANT TREE
WHICH HAD A FRAGMENT
OF THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL
EMBEDDED IN IT.
SINCE MY CREATION,
I HAVE CRAVED HUMAN FLESH
AND DEVOURED MY VICTIMS.
BUT NOW, I WISH TO HAVE
A LIVING BODY THAT WILL NOT ROT.
FOR THAT, I REQUIRE MORE POWER
FROM THE SACRED JEWEL.
- I SEE.
SO THAT'S WHY THE MASK
IS SO DESPERATE
TO HAVE THESE SHARDS.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY HUMANS
YOU'VE EATEN SO FAR,
BUT IT'S TIME
TO LOSE SOME WEIGHT!
WHAT THE...
- YOU FELL INTO MY TRAP.
NOW YOU SHALL NEVER ESCAPE ME.
- AAH!
[GASP]
- INUYASHA!
[GRUNTING]
- I SHOULD'VE KNOWN BETTER.
- AAH!
UHH!
- KAGOME!
- UHH! UHH!
I CAN'T LET THIS THING
GET THE JEWELS!
SOTA, TAKE THESE SHARDS AND RUN!
- OK.
- HURRY!
- UHH--UHH.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- IT'S RIGHT BEHIND YOU!
- AAH! UHH.
THE MASK IS AFTER THIS BOTTLE.
I'LL THROW IT AWAY.
NO, THAT WON'T WORK.
I CAN'T LET IT HAVE
THESE JEWELS!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- AAH!
- UHH!
DON'T MOVE, KID!
- YAA!
- AAH! AAH!
UHH!
UHH.
[CLINK]
- YOU DESTROYED THE MASK!
YOU DID IT!
- SURE THING.
YOU STILL GOT THOSE
JEWEL FRAGMENTS?
[GULP]
HMM...YEAH.
- INUYASHA!
- HEY, KAGOME.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
HOW'S YOUR HAND?
- UH, FINE.
OK, THIS IS WEIRD.
WHEN DID INUYASHA
START BEING SO NICE?
I MEAN, NOT SO NICE,
BUT KIND OF NICE.
AND MAYBE IT'S JUST
THE MORNING LIGHT,
BUT HE LOOKS PRETTY COOL
STANDING THERE WITH HIS SWORD.
WAIT A MINUTE.
MORNING LIGHT?
OH, NO!
IT'S MORNING ALREADY, AND I
HAVEN'T STUDIED FOR MY TEST!
OHH!
- HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- THANKS, INUYASHA.
IT'S BEEN A SLICE.
SEE YOU WHEN I SEE YA.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
OH, AND SOTA, DON'T FORGET
TO PICK UP THOSE JEWEL SHARDS
AND BRING THEM HOME WITH YOU.
INUYASHA, I'M GOING
TO BE SUPER MAD
IF YOU'RE STILL AROUND
WHEN I GET BACK FROM SCHOOL.
- HMM?
- KNOW WHAT?
I'VE GOT A NEW HERO,
BET YOU CAN'T GUESS WHO IT IS.
- OH, MAN.
- IN EVERY
RIGHT-ANGLED TRIANGLE,
THE SQUARE ON THE HYPOTENUSE
IS EQUAL TO THE SUM
OF THE SQUARES.
OH, I'LL NEVER REMEMBER
ALL THIS IN TIME!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- WE FOUND OUT THAT
THE SACRED JEWEL FRAGMENTS EXIST
EVEN IN THE PRESENT-DAY WORLD.
THE SEARCH FOR THE SHARDS
IS GETTING
MORE AND MORE COMPLICATED
ALL THE TIME.
OH, NO.
I HAVE TO TAKE SOTA
TO THE HOSPITAL.
SPARE ME.
DEALING WITH INUYASHA
IS ENOUGH OF A HEADACHE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHO'S THAT LITTLE GIRL,
AND WHAT DOES SHE WANT?
I'VE GOT TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO HELP HER.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.