>> THAT PLACE THAT KANTA'S
FATHER SAW.
I WONDER IF HAKUDOSHI ALREADY
KNOWS ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE COULD IT BE THOUGH,
THIS PLACE THAT'S COVERED
IN WHITE MIST AND STREWN WITH
GIANT BONES?
>> I THINK I MIGHT HAVE BEEN TO
THAT PLACE ONCE BEFORE ACTUALLY.
>> INUYASHA'S THINKING THE SAME
THING I AM.
WHITE MIST AND GIANT BONES.
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT.
THE GRAVE OF INUYASHA'S FATHER.
>> THIS PLACE.
OF COURSE.
I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE.
OLD MAN.
HUH?
HAH, I SUPPOSE YOU'RE HAPPY,
TETSAIGA.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE
YOU'VE SEEN HIM.
OLD MAN, REST ASSURED I'VE BEEN
USING THE TETSAIGA TO ITS
FULLEST!
UH!
HUH?
IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT.
IF THAT'S WHERE THE SHARD OF
THE SACRED JEWEL LIES,
THEN THAT'S WHERE I'LL GO.
SO, HE WANTS ME TO VISIT HIS
GRAVE, DOES HE?
>> WHERE COULD INUYASHA HAVE
GONE?
>> MAYBE HE WENT TO LOOK FOR
MYOGA.
>> MYOGA?
BUT HOW IS HE GONNA FIND SOMEONE
WHO'S SO TINY?
>> OH, I GUESS IT'S NOT GONNA
BE EASY.
>> KAGOME, WHY DO YOU THINK
INUYASHA MIGHT BE LOOKING
FOR MYOGA?
>> I CAN'T REALLY SAY FOR SURE,
BUT IT'S PROBABLY ABOUT
THE BLACK PEARL.
>> THE BLACK PEARL?
>> HEY, YOU THERE, TOTOSAI?
TOTOSAI, YOU'RE HERE, AIN'T YOU?
ANSWER ME!
>> OH, IT'S YOU.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> YOU'RE NOT THE ONE I WANT
TO TALK TO.
NOW, WHERE'S MYOGA?
>> TAKE IT EASY.
YOU'RE BEING RUDE, AS USUAL.
>> FRESH BLOOD!
[SLURPS]
AHH.
IT MUST BE SERIOUS FOR YOU
TO COME THIS FAR LOOKING FOR ME.
SO WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU,
MASTER?
UH!
THAT REALLY HURT, YOU KNOW.
>> SO THIS BLACK PEARL IS A WAY
TO INUYASHA'S FATHER'S GRAVE AND
THE BORDER TO THE NETHERWORLD?
>> YES.
WE KNEW THE TETSAIGA WAS TO BE
FOUND AT HIS FATHER'S GRAVE.
WHEN WE WENT TO GET THE SWORD,
THE BLACK PEARL CREATED A
PASSAGEWAY WHICH CONNECTED TO
THE OTHER WORLD.
>> YOU REALIZE SESSHOMARU'S
THERE.
AAH!
>> AFTER HE TOOK POSSESSION
OF THE TETSAIGA, WE RETURNED
TO THIS WORLD.
AND THE BLACK PEARL FELL
STRAIGHT BACK INTO INUYASHA'S
RIGHT EYE.
>> I SEE.
YOU WANT TO FIND A WAY TO REMOVE
THE BLACK PEARL FROM YOUR EYE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO DO IT?
>> IT'S NOT QUITE THAT EASY.
YOU SEE, WHEN THE BLACK PEARL
ALLOWED YOU PASSAGE INTO
THE NETHERWORLD, IT SERVED
ITS PURPOSE.
NOW IT HAS BECOME A PERMANENT
PART OF YOUR EYE, AND IT
NO LONGER HAS ANY DEMONIC POWER.
>> [SIGHS]
SO I CAN'T USE IT ANYMORE?
>> NO, YOU CANNOT.
>> DAMN!
THEN THE HOW THE HELL AM I
SUPPOSED TO GET TO MY OLD MAN'S
GRAVE?
>> YOU WANT TO GO TO YOUR
FATHER'S GRAVE?
>> YES!
>> GOOD BOY!
SO YOU FINALLY REALIZED HOW
GREAT A MAN YOUR FATHER WAS
AND HAVE DECIDED TO PAY YOUR
RESPECTS AT HIS GRAVE.
I'M VERY HAPPY YOU'VE FINALLY
GROWN UP!
>> DON'T EVER HIT ME LIKE THAT.
>> YOU ALWAYS HIT ME THOUGH.
IT'S HARDLY FAIR.
>> I AGREE WITH TOTOSAI.
IT'S QUITE A SURPRISE TO SEE
THAT YOU'RE SHOWING SUCH
RESPECT, INUYASHA.
>> HA!
DON'T GO GETTING ALL WEEPY.
I THINK THAT A SHARD OF THE
SACRED JEWEL MAY BE THERE
SOMEWHERE.
SO I HAVE TO GET TO THE
NETHERWORLD SOMEHOW AND FIND IT
BEFORE HE DOES.
>> A SACRED JEWEL SHARD?
>> IF I CAN'T USE THE BLACK
PEARL, I'LL HAVE TO FIND SOME
OTHER WAY.
SO TELL ME.
HOW CAN I GET TO THE
NETHERWORLD?
>> HMM.
HMM.
>> HMM?
>> FOOL!
>> HEY, WHO YOU CALLIN' FOOL?
>> THINK ABOUT IT FOR A MINUTE.
THAT DEMON GRAVEYARD IS IN A
DIFFERENT WORLD REACHED ONLY
BY TRAVELING DOWN A MYSTERIOUS
AND ELUSIVE PATHWAY.
IN THAT CASE, HOW DO YOU SUPPOSE
A SACRED JEWEL SHARD COULD HAVE
GOTTEN THERE?
>> HE'S QUITE RIGHT,
MASTER INUYASHA.
AND DON'T FORGET, KAGOME
WAS WITH YOU WHEN YOU WERE
AT THE DEMON GRAVEYARD BEFORE,
YET SHE DIDN'T SENSE A SACRED
JEWEL SHARD AT ALL, EVEN WITH
HER ACUTE POWERS.
>> BUT THAT WAS WAY BACK THEN.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'D BE ANY
DIFFERENT THIS TIME.
>> SHUT UP, MYOGA.
LOOK, ARE YOU GONNA TAKE ME
TO THE DEMON GRAVEYARD,
OR AREN'T YOU?
>> IN ORDER TO GET TO THE
GRAVEYARD, YOU MUST SEE HOSENKI
FIRST.
>> HOSENKI, HUH?
WHO THE HELL IS THAT?
>> HOSENKI IS AN OLD FRIEND OF
YOUR FATHER.
HE CULTIVATES MANY KINDS OF
PRECIOUS JEWELS, AND EACH ONE OF
THEM CAN SERVE AS A PASSAGEWAY
TO THE DEMON GRAVEYARD AT THE
BORDER TO THE NETHERWORLD.
>> HUH?
SO HE MADE INUYASHA'S
BLACK PEARL, TOO?
>> YES, HE DID.
IT WAS ORIGINALLY GIVEN TO
INUYASHA'S FATHER BY HOSENKI.
LISTEN.
THE DEMON GRAVEYARD IS THE FINAL
RESTING PLACE OF THE DEAD.
IT'S NO PLACE FOR THE LIVING.
PLEASE RECONSIDER, MASTER.
>> HUH!
IF THAT'S WHERE THE JEWEL SHARD
IS, THEN THAT'S WHERE WE'RE
GONNA GO.
YOU GOT IT?
>> INUYASHA, YOU'RE FINALLY
MAKING YOUR MOVE.
>> I'VE JUST ABOUT HAD IT.
HOW LONG MUST I BABY-SIT
THIS CREEPY LITTLE KID?
IF I KILL HIM RIGHT HERE
AND NOW, I'LL BE FREE.
HMM?
[GASPS]
>> KAGURA...
DON'T YOU REALIZE I CAN READ
YOUR THOUGHTS AS PLAINLY AS
AN OPEN BOOK?
YOU SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL.
>> [SIGHS]
YOU WIN...
THIS TIME.
>> [GRUNTING]
LORD SESSHOMARU,
WHERE ARE WE HEADED?
DID YOU HEAR ME,
LORD SESSHOMARU?
>> DO NOT ASK ME, JAKEN.
>> HUH?
THEN WHO, PRAY TELL,
SHOULD I ASK?
HOW ABOUT YOU, AH-UN?
I'M SURE RIN DOESN'T KNOW
ANYTHING.
>> THAT BOY'S SCENT AND THE
SCENT THAT I SMELL BEYOND HIM.
NARAKU.
THIS IS IT.
>> HMM?
>> THIS TIME I SHALL KILL HIM.
>> AH!
>> MASTER JAKEN, BETTER NOT ASK
HIM UNNECESSARY QUESTIONS,
OR ELSE HE SAID THAT HE'S GOING
TO KILL YOU.
>> OK.
>> DAMN IT!
HOW MUCH LONGER, MYOGA?
>> NOT TOO FAR NOW.
ONCE WE GET THROUGH THIS VALLEY,
WE'LL REACH THE MARSH WHERE
HOSENKI LIVES.
>> THE SUN'S ALMOST SETTING,
AND WE'RE STILL NOT THERE.
>> DON'T YOU THINK MAYBE IT'S
TIME FOR A REST?
>> HA!
NO REST FOR THE WICKED,
I ALWAYS SAY.
[GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA, WAIT!
>> HE NEVER REALLY WAS ONE
TO LISTEN.
IDIOT.
>> NO STUPID CLIFF IS GONNA
SLOW ME DOWN, 'CAUSE I--HUH?
>> MASTER INUYASHA, THIS IS
IMPOSSIBLE EVEN FOR YOU.
WHY DON'T YOU WAIT FOR KILALA?
>> HA, YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
NOTHING'S IMPOSSIBLE.
IT JUST TAKES A LITTLE SUBTLE
SKILL AND INGENUITY.
CHECK THIS OUT!
WIND SCAR!
>> AVALANCHE!
>> HA!
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
>> TRULY AMAZING, MASTER.
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT ALL
ALONG.
>> YOU'RE A LIAR.
>> YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> WATCH OUT!
AAH!
>> INUYASHA IS ALWAYS SO
IMPULSIVE.
>> THAT'S FOR SURE.
HEY, SHIPPO, LET'S KEEP GOING,
OK?
>> YEAH!
ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU BASTARD!
>> [LAUGHING]
>> HAKUDOSHI.
[GROWLS]
>> [GROWLS]
>> YOU'VE BEEN RATHER
CARELESS.
>> SO, HAKUDOSHI, I TAKE IT
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING HERE FOR US.
WELL, GO AHEAD AND ATTACK.
GO ON.
BUT REMEMBER KILLING ME IS NOT
GONNA BE AS EASY AS YOU THINK.
>> I HAVE NO INTENTION OF
KILLING YOU.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE IF YOU WERE
GONNA FIGURE OUT YOU NEEDED
TO GO TO HOSENKI'S PLACE,
AND YOU ACTUALLY DID.
I'M IMPRESSED.
>> DAMN IT.
YOU KNOW ABOUT HOSENKI?
>> BUT AS FATE WOULD HAVE IT,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO SEE
HOSENKI.
>> WHAT?
YOU MEAN--OH, NO.
YOU DIDN'T.
>> DON'T START JUMPING TO
CONCLUSIONS, INUYASHA.
I WON'T MEDDLE WITH YOU
OR YOUR FRIENDS.
AFTER ALL, I DON'T WANT THE FUN
TO END SO SOON.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT,
INUYASHA.
YOU AND YOUR FRIEND OR ME?
WHO DO YOU THINK WILL BE
THE FIRST TO REACH THE BORDER
BETWEEN THIS WORLD AND THE NEXT?
>> GET BACK HERE, DAMN IT!
>> HA HA HA HA!
>> YOU BASTARD!
>> INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
>> IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
>> NO, NOTHING'S WRONG.
LET'S GO.
>> HUH?
>> I DON'T SEE ANYTHING HERE,
YOU GUYS.
>> HELLO?
HOSENKI, ARE YOU THERE?
HELLO?
ANSWER ME.
WHERE ARE YOU?
HOSENKI!
>> HUH?
>> THAT MUST BE HIM!
>> AH!
>> KILALA, PLEASE GET BACK!
>> AAH!
>> OH, IT'S YOU, HOSENKI.
>> WHO IS IT?
THERE ARE NO JEWELS HERE.
>> HUH?
>> HOSENKI, IT'S ME--MYOGA.
IT'S ME.
>> OHH.
MASTER MYOGA, IT'S YOU.
>> SO THIS GUY'S HOSENKI?
>> NOT TRUE.
I AM IN FACT HOSENKI'S SON.
MY FATHER IS NOW DEAD.
>> WHAT?
>> HOSENKI'S DEAD?
>> BUT THAT MUST MEAN--TELL US
WHO KILLED HIM.
>> NO, NO, NO.
HE DIED JUST RECENTLY
OF OLD AGE.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> OF OLD AGE?
>> MY FATHER DIED PEACEFULLY,
AND SO NOW IT SEEMS I AM
THE NEW HOSENKI.
>> UM, YOU SAID THERE ARE
NO JEWELS THAT CAN LEAD US
TO THE GRAVE?
>> CORRECT.
MY FATHER USED ALL THE JEWELS
BEFORE HE PASSED AWAY.
AND SO I AM CURRENTLY IN THE
PROCESS OF MAKING NEW JEWELS.
>> NO PROBLEM.
LET US HAVE THOSE ONES.
>> MASTER INUYASHA, PLEASE SHOW
OUR HOST SOME MANNERS.
>> I'LL TAKE THE JEWELS BY FORCE
IF I HAVE TO.
>> OH, BROTHER.
>> HE'S SO TACTFUL.
>> PLEASE, I BEG OF YOU,
MASTER HOSENKI.
WE DESPERATELY NEED THOSE
PRECIOUS JEWELS.
>> HMM.
WELL, I DON'T MIND GIVING
THEM TO YOU.
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO WAIT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
>> OH, WE'LL WAIT.
>> HOW LONG WE TALKING?
>> 100 YEARS.
>> YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
>> I'M STILL ONLY AN APPRENTICE
JEWEL MAKER.
>> INUYASHA ISN'T RENOWNED FOR
HIS PATIENCE.
>> THAT, I FEAR,
IS AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
>> DAMN IT.
ISN'T THERE ANY OTHER WAY?
WHILE WE'RE WASTING TIME HERE,
NARAKU OR THAT KID HAKUDOSHI
CAN GET TO THE SHARD FIRST.
>> SO TELL ME.
DID YOU HAVE ANY LUCK?
WERE YOU ABLE TO FIND THE WAY
TO THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT?
>> YES.
ALTHOUGH THERE'S ONLY 1 PATH
AT THIS TIME.
>> HMM.
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
PERHAPS WE SHOULD BE GOING.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> THERE'S ONLY 1 WAY.
THE GATE MUST BE FORCED OPEN.
>> HEY, HAKUDOSHI.
>> HMM, INTERESTING.
KAGURA?
>> HUH?
>> I NEED YOU TO GO ON
AN ERRAND.
>> ERRAND?
>> THE SCENT DISAPPEARED.
DID I LET HIM SLIP AWAY?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU?
AH!
OH, IT'S NOTHING, MY LORD.
NOTHING.
SORRY.
[GROANS]
I'VE BEEN ON PINS AND NEEDLES
LATELY.
>> MASTER JAKEN, YOU SHOULD
PRACTICE AND LEARN TO TURN EACH
ONE OF YOUR SIGHS INTO PRETTY
LITTLE FLOWERS BECAUSE THEN
THERE WOULD BE FLOWERS
EVERYWHERE!
>> BE QUIET, GIRL!
HMM?
>> HMM?
>> OH, PLEASE DON'T LEAVE US!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> SEEMS AS IF WE'VE REACHED
A DEAD END.
>> THERE'S NOT MUCH WE CAN DO.
WE CAN'T WAIT FOR 100 YEARS.
>> [SIGHS]
>> COME ON, MYOGA.
THINK HARD.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T KNOW
OF ANY OTHER WAY TO GET TO
THE GRAVEYARD?
>> OH, FOR THE LAST TIME,
THERE IS NO OTHER WAY TO REACH
THE GRAVEYARD, OK!
>> SO, INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> YOU WOULD LIKE TO KNOW WHERE
THE PATHWAY IS?
>> HEH, KAGURA.
>> HAKUDOSHI IS HEADED TOWARD
THE MOUNTAIN IN THE REALM
OF FIRE.
THERE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
A GATEWAY THERE THAT LEADS
THE TRAVELER TO THE BORDER
BETWEEN THIS WORLD AND THE NEXT.
>> MOUNTAIN IN THE REALM
OF FIRE?
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND, KAGURA.
WHY HAVE YOU COME TO TELL US
THIS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'D HAVE TO ASK HAKUDOSHI
THAT.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
WAS THAT A MESSAGE FROM
HAKUDOSHI?
>> IT COULD BE A TRAP.
>> HA!
I DON'T CARE IF IT IS A TRAP.
>> DON'T EVEN THINK OF IT,
MASTER.
THE MOUNTAIN IN THE REALM
OF FIRE IS TOO DANGEROUS.
YOU MUST NEVER, EVER GO TO THAT
PLACE.
>> HUH!
JUDGING FROM YOUR REACTION,
MYOGA, I'M GUESSING THAT THIS
LITTLE TIDBIT ABOUT A GATEWAY
IS THE TRUTH, AM I RIGHT?
>> WELL, I--MAY--
WELL, I SUPPOSE IT COULD--
>> HA!
THAT MEANS WE HAVE TO GO
REGARDLESS OF WHAT SURPRISES
HAKUDOSHI MIGHT HAVE IN STORE
FOR US.
>> THIS IS TURNING OUT TO BE
QUITE ENTERTAINING.
[LAUGHS]
INUYASHA, I SHALL LET YOU PASS
THROUGH THE GATE BEFORE ME...
IN EXCHANGE FOR YOUR LIFE.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ I GET, I GET, I GET
GET THE FEELING
I GET, I GET, I GET
GET THE DREAMING ♪
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ♪ COME MY WAY ♪
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ♪ COME CLOSE TO ME ♪
♪ I'LL BE WITH YOU
I'LL BE WITH YOU
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
SO COME MY WAY ♪
>> ♪ COME MY WAY ♪
>> IN THE REALM OF FIRE
IS THE GATEWAY WE SEEK.
THE GIANT STATUES THAT WE FIND
THERE BEGIN TO MOVE.
>> THOSE TWO ARE GOZU AND MEZU,
THE GUARDIANS OF THIS GATE.
ONLY THE DEAD CAN PASS THROUGH
THE GATE.
>> IF YOU WISH TO PASS, THEN YOU
MUST BE KILLED BY THE GUARDIANS.
>> WHAT?
THE WIND SCAR HAS NO EFFECT
ON THEM.
>> THEY CANNOT BE HARMED BY
A BLADE OF THIS WORLD.
>> NEXT TIME, BIZARRE GUARDS
AT THE BORDER OF THE AFTERLIFE.
>> I NEED YOU TO DIE, INUYASHA,
SO THAT THE GATE WILL OPEN.