>> THIS ARROW BROKE THE BARRIER.
>> INUYASHA'S RED TETSUSAIGA
COULDN'T BREAK THROUGH
HAKUDOSHI'S BARRIER,
YET THIS ARROW DID.
THERE'S ONLY ONE PERSON
IT COULD BELONG TO.
KIKYO MUST BE ALIVE.
>> IT ISN'T KIKYO'S.
>> NOBODY SAID THE ARROW
BELONGED TO HER.
>> BUT YOU'RE ALL THINKING IT.
I HAVE TO ADMIT, I WONDERED THE
SAME THING MYSELF AT FIRST.
THIS ARROW DOESN'T HAVE
KIKYO'S SCENT.
IT'S TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
WHAT IS THIS SMELL?
I DON'T KNOW WHO IT
WAS FIRED BY, BUT IT DEFINITELY
WASN'T ONE OF OUR ALLIES.
>> SO IT DOESN'T BELONG
TO ANY OF OUR FRIENDS.
>> RIGHT.
NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT, AROUND
THE TIME THAT ARROW WAS FIRED
AT THE BARRIER, I DIDN'T SENSE
KIKYO'S SPIRITUAL POWERS AT ALL.
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
IF IT WASN'T FIRED BY KIKYO,
THEN WHO FIRED IT?
THAT ARROW SAVED INUYASHA,
REMEMBER?
>> PERHAPS I KNOW.
>> HUH?
>> IT COULD HAVE BEEN A
FRIENDLY HAND LENT BY HIJIRI,
THE HOLY ONE.
>> YES, DEFINITELY.
>> YOU COULD BE RIGHT ABOUT
THAT.
>> HIJIRI, THE HOLY ONE.
>> WE'D BETTER HURRY TO SEE
THIS HIJIRI PERSON.
SOMETHING TELLS ME THE BIRDS'LL
BE HEADED THAT WAY, TOO.
>> MASTER, WE ARE
ALMOST AT THE VILLAGE.
I ONLY HOPE THAT THEY SOMEHOW
MANAGED TO HOLD OUT.
>> PEOPLE, STAY WHERE YOU ARE
AND DO NOT MOVE FROM THE CAVE.
>> ARE YOU CERTAIN WE'LL BE
SAFE FROM THOSE BIRDS?
>> WHAT IF THEY BREAK THROUGH
THE BARRIER AND COME INTO THE
CAVE?
>> WHEN WILL HIJIRI THE HOLY
ONE RETURN?
>> THEY PUT UP A BARRIER?
SUCH INSOLENCE.
FAIRLY STRONG FOR SOMETHING
THAT WAS CREATED BY HUMANS.
IN THAT CASE, PERHAPS I SHOULD
FORCE THEM TO COME
OUT OF THE CAVE.
AFTER THEM.
>> THE BIRDS ARE AFLAME.
>> WE'RE COMPLETELY SURROUNDED
BY FIRE.
>> WE'LL BE BURNED ALIVE UNLESS
HELP COMES FAST.
>> I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
>> LOOK, THIS SIDE
ISN'T BURNING.
RUN FOR IT.
>> QUICKLY.
>> HEED MY COMMAND.
DO NOT LEAVE THE BARRIER.
>> [SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY]
>> HIJIRI THE HOLY ONE
HAS RETURNED.
>> HURRY, PLEASE SAVE US.
>> THE ONE WHO ERECTED THE
BARRIER.
SLAY HIM.
>> LOOK, LOOK, WE'RE SAVED.
>> MY BIRDS HAVE ALL BEEN SLAIN.
HOW ON EARTH COULD THIS HAVE
HAPPENED?
EVER SINCE NARAKU CAME INTO THE
PICTURE, I'VE HAD NOTHING
BUT INTERFERENCE.
>> SHE'S GONE.
>> ALL THANKS TO THE SAINT
HIJIRI.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU FOR SAVING US.
>> SAINT HIJIRI.
>> WE'VE JUST PASSED THE SUMMIT.
WE SHOULD REACH THE HOLY ONE'S
VILLAGE ANY TIME NOW.
>> ONCE WE REACH THE VILLAGE,
WE MIGHT JUST FIND OUT
WHO THIS HIJIRI PERSON
REALLY IS.
>> THERE IT IS.
>> YEAH.
HMM.
I SMELL BLOOD AND SOMETHING
BURNING.
>> WHAT?
>> IT'S COMING FROM AROUND THAT
CRAGGY MOUNTAIN UP AHEAD.
>> LET'S HURRY, THEN.
INCREDIBLE.
>> YES, THE SAINT HIJIRI
SLEW THE BIRD DEMONS.
>> WE'RE SO VERY GRATEFUL.
>> THE HOLY ONE SAVED US
VILLAGERS BY WIPING OUT A WHOLE
FLOCK OF DEMON BIRDS
WITH A SINGLE ARROW.
>> A SINGLE ARROW?
REALLY? THAT'S AMAZING.
BUT THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
I MEAN, IS HIJIRI STILL HERE?
>> NO, I'M AFRAID NOT.
THE HOLY ONE HAS ALREADY LEFT.
>> HUH?
>> THE HOLY ONE HAS LEFT TO
TRACK DOWN AND DESTROY
THE DEMON BIRDS.
WE ARE SO FORTUNATE
FOR HIS HELP.
>> WE CAME HERE AS QUICKLY AS
WE COULD, YET WE JUST
MISSED HIM.
>> INUYASHA, DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD FOLLOW?
>> AFTER THIS HIJIRI, YOU MEAN?
>> JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
IT COULD TURN OUT TO BE KIKYO,
YOU KNOW.
>> HUH?
>> KAGOME.
>> INUYASHA.
>> KIKYO WAS KILLED BY NARAKU.
I DIDN'T ACTUALLY SEE HER DIE,
AND I DIDN'T SEE HER BODY.
KIKYO, IF YOU ARE STILL ALIVE,
WHY HAVEN'T YOU COME TO FIND ME?
KAGOME.
>> KAGOME IS SO BRAVE.
I'LL GIVE HER THAT MUCH.
HOW COULD SHE SPEAK UP
LIKE THAT?
>> YOU MEAN WHAT SHE SAID ABOUT
KIKYO?
SANGO, IF THIS GREAT HIJIRI
TURNS OUT TO BE KIKYO,
THEN WE'RE SURE TO CROSS PATHS.
OUR GOALS ARE THE SAME--TO FIND
THE NESTS OF THE DEMON BIRDS.
>> YES, BUT THAT'S NOT THE
PROBLEM.
INUYASHA GETS SO INDECISIVE
AROUND KIKYO.
KAGOME'S PUT UP WITH IT UNTIL
NOW, BUT WHO KNOWS HOW LONG
IT'LL LAST?
IF I WERE HER, I'D PUSH HIM
OVER A CLIFF AND MAKE SURE
HE NEVER WALKS AGAIN.
>> UH, YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT
INUYASHA, AREN'T YOU?
>> OHH! SHE'S SERIOUS.
OHH!
>> KAGOME, ARE YOU OK WITH THIS?
>> WHY WOULDN'T I BE?
HOW ABOUT YOU?
WHAT IF SAINT HIJIRI TURNS OUT
TO BE KIKYO AFTER ALL?
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
>> BLUNT AS USUAL.
>> ONE THING, THOUGH.
IF IT REALLY IS HER, THEN
OBVIOUSLY NARAKU DIDN'T KILL
KIKYO LIKE HE SET OUT TO DO.
AND IF THAT'S THE CASE, HE'LL
DEFINITELY COME AND TRY TO KILL
HER AGAIN.
FOR NOW, I SAY WE CONCENTRATE
ON FINDING THE BIRDS' NEST
AND DESTROYING THEM.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'LL REGRET DOING
THIS, YOU MEDDLING FOOL.
HOW DID YOU BREAK THROUGH MY
BARRIER?
>> WHAT A TOUGH LITTLE BRAT.
AM I HALLUCINATING?
NO, IT'S TRUE.
I CAN HEAR HIS HEART,
BUT HE'S HOLLOW INSIDE.
IS HIS HEART SOMEWHERE ELSE,
THEN?
>> LADY KAEDE, LADY KAEDE,
TERRIBLE NEWS.
>> WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
>> WELL, THERE WAS A LIGHT IN
THE SKY THAT FELL.
>> THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
ARE YOU CERTAIN ABOUT THIS?
>> YES.
>> AND WHERE EXACTLY DID YOU
SEE THIS MYSTERIOUS LIGHT?
>> A FEW MOMENTS AGO.
WE SAW IT FALLING FROM THE SKY.
IT DESCENDED TOWARD LADY
KIKYO'S SHRINE.
>> IT WHAT?
>> OVER THERE.
>> ARE THEY DEMONS?
>> LADY KAEDE, WHAT ARE THEY?
>> I'M NOT CERTAIN,
BUT THEY WEREN'T DEMONS.
PROBABLY MORE LIKE SHIKIGAMI
MESSENGERS SENT BY SOMEONE.
I DIDN'T SENSE ANY EVIL AURA
FROM THEM.
>> LADY KAEDE.
>> HUH?
>> COME, TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE THOSE BEINGS
FROM THE LIGHT WERE DIGGING
HERE.
>> WHAT?
>> NOT SURPRISING.
KIKYO'S ASHES AND SOIL FROM HER
GRAVE WERE TAKEN ONCE BEFORE,
REMEMBER?
>> NOT AGAIN.
>> HMM.
WHO WOULD TAKE SOIL FROM SISTER
KIKYO'S GRAVE, AND WHY?
>> NARAKU'S DEMONS.
>> IT LOOKS TO ME LIKE THEY'RE
SEARCHING FOR SOMETHING.
>> MY GUESS IS THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR HIJIRI THE HOLY ONE.
>> YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
I BET THIS HIJIRI'S
GETTING IN NARAKU'S WAY.
>> IF THAT'S THE CASE, THEN
MAYBE NARAKU REALIZES THAT
SAINT HIJIRI MIGHT BE KIKYO,
AND IF THAT'S TRUE, THEN I
WONDER IF HE'S GONNA TRY TO
FIND HER AND KILL HER AGAIN.
>> HIJIRI, YOU SAY?
YES, I'VE CERTAINLY HEARD
RUMORS OF THE HOLY ONE.
>> WE HEARD THAT HE MIGHT HAVE
BEEN SEEN IN THE VICINITY
LATELY.
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT I DID SEE
SOMETHING THAT COULD BE A SIGN
FROM HIM.
IT WAS JUST BEFORE DAWN, AND TWO
STRANGE STREAKS OF LIGHT
APPEARED IN THE SKY.
IT'S AS THOUGH THEY WERE SUCKED
TOWARD THE FORBIDDEN MOUNTAIN.
>> IT'S FORBIDDEN.
HOW SO?
>> 'CAUSE ONLY THE CHOSEN ONES
ARE ALLOWED TO GO
TO THE MOUNTAIN.
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO THERE,
INUYASHA?
>> YEAH.
MIGHT AS WELL.
IT'S OUR ONLY LEAD.
>> SANGO, I THOUGHT WE WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE LOOKING
FOR THE DEMON BIRDS' NEST.
>> HUH?
>> IT'S NOT LIKE IT MATTERS
TO ME OR ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST THAT SOMEWHERE ALONG
THE WAY, OUR GOALS CHANGED FROM
DESTROYING THE BIRDS TO MEETING
THIS HIJIRI PERSON.
>> SHIPPO, PLEASE MAKE SURE YOU
DON'T MENTION THAT IN FRONT OF
KAGOME.
>> I'M SURE SHE'S ALREADY
NOTICED IT HERSELF BY NOW.
>> THERE'S THE MOUNTAIN.
>> HEY, INUYASHA, LOOK AT THAT.
SOMETHING'S SPARKLING.
WATER, MAYBE.
>> YEAH, COULD BE A WATERFALL.
>> DEMONS ARE COMING.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR SAINT
HIJIRI.
>> HMM.
INUYASHA, HAVE YOU NOTICED
THEM AROUND US?
>> YEAH.
NARAKU'S DEMONS AGAIN.
SOMETHING TELLS ME THEY'RE
FOLLOWING US.
OR EVEN WORSE.
>> THERE ARE MORE AND MORE OF
THEM COMING EVERY MINUTE.
>> YEAH, GOING OUR DIRECTION.
SO IF THAT'S THE CASE, THEY
MUST BE HEADING TOWARD THE
FORBIDDEN MOUNTAIN.
DOES THAT MEAN KIKYO IS THERE?
>> HUH?
>> A SACRED ARROW.
>> SAINT HIJIRI IS HERE
ON THIS MOUNTAIN.
>> WE'D BETTER HURRY.
>> THEY'RE COMING FROM
DOWN HERE AS WELL.
>> [INDISTINCT]
>> MOVE.
WHAT A PAIN.
MIROKU, SANGO,
TAKE CARE OF KAGOME.
GO ON AHEAD.
>> INUYASHA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I'LL JOIN YOU AS SOON AS I
DESTROY THESE VERMIN.
YOU GUYS GO AND FIND THAT
HIJIRI PERSON.
GET GOING.
>> KIRARA.
>> INUYASHA.
>> SHOULD WE REALLY SEE HIJIRI
BEFORE HE DOES?
>> WHAT'LL I DO IF THIS HIJIRI
PERSON TURNS OUT TO BE KIKYO?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT FIRST THINGS FIRST.
[INDISTINCT]
I HAVE TO FIND OUT FOR
MYSELF OR I WON'T BE ABLE TO
GET ON WITH MY LIFE.
HUH?
IS THAT KIKYO?
I'M NOT PICKING UP HER SCENT.
STILL.
SHOW YOURSELF.
LET ME SEE YOUR FACE.
>> I'M KIND OF WORRIED.
THINK INUYASHA'S OK?
>> HE'LL COME AS SOON AS HE'S
DONE.
>> SHE'S RIGHT.
HE'LL COME.
HE'S THE ONE WHO WANTS TO MEET
HIJIRI MORE THAN ANYONE.
>> SANGO, HERE COMES
SOME MORE DEMONS.
>> KAGOME, SHIPPO,
YOU STAY HERE.
>> RIGHT.
>> KIRARA.
>> [INDISTINCT]
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M HERE WITH YOU, KAGOME.
I'VE GOT TO KEEP IT TOGETHER.
HELP!
KAGOME! DEMONS!
>> HANG ON A MINUTE.
THEY'RE SOUL COLLECTORS.
>> HEY, WAIT, KAGOME.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> SO, KIKYO REALLY IS HERE.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> AFTER THOSE SOUL COLLECTORS.
KIKYO MIGHT BE UP THERE.
>> DON'T BE SO HASTY.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
>> SHE DISAPPEARED.
>> A BARRIER.
>> ANSWER ME.
ARE YOU KIKYO OR NOT?
>> A POTENT AURA HAS RAVAGED MY
MASTER'S FLESH.
HER BODY CANNOT RESTORE ITSELF.
>> SHE HAS ALSO LOST HER VOICE.
SHE FIGHTS USING HER SPIRIT
ALONE.
HOWEVER, SOON HER STRENGTH
WILL RUN OUT.
>> SO BACK THEN, SHE DIDN'T DIE?
KIKYO?
YOU ARE KIKYO.
KIKYO.
KIKYO!
HUH?
ISN'T THIS A SHIKIGAMI?
>> DAMN, THAT KIKYO IS ELUSIVE,
ISN'T SHE?
>> KAGURA?
YOU AGAIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON AROUND HERE?
>> JUST WHAT I'D LIKE TO KNOW.
WHAT A WASTE OF MY TIME.
>> WHERE IS KIKYO?
IS SHE STILL ALIVE OR NOT?
>> HMM. NARAKU
SEEMS TO THINK SO.
YOU KNOW THE ARROW THAT BROKE
THROUGH HAKUDOSHI'S BARRIER?
THERE WAS SOME DIRT LEFT ON THE
ARROWHEAD, AND IT CAME FROM
ONIGUMO'S CAVE.
>> ONIGUMO?
OF COURSE.
THAT WAS THE SCENT
FROM THE ARROW.
>> THE SOIL THERE IS IMMERSED
WITH ONIGUMO'S LUST FOR KIKYO.
AND THAT'S WHAT PROTECTS KIKYO
FROM BEING DESTROYED BY
NARAKU'S WRATH.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE WHO COULD
HAVE ANY USE FOR SOIL FROM
ONIGUMO'S CAVE.
IN ANY CASE, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE BOTH BEEN CHASING ALL
OVER THE COUNTRYSIDE AFTER A
FAKE.
TILL NEXT TIME.
NARAKU'S GREATEST HINDRANCE
IS STILL ALIVE.
NOW, THIS IS GETTING
INTERESTING.
>> HUH?
THOSE TWO GIRLS--
THEY'VE GONE, TOO.
>> IS KIKYO REALLY ALIVE?
>> IT'S TRUE, THEN.
KIKYO IS ALIVE SOMEWHERE.
>> ARE THEY CALLING ME?
IS THAT IT?
A WATERFALL.
KIKYO.
>> [MUSIC]
>> ALONE AT THE BASE OF
THE MOUNTAIN,
I MEET THE HOLY PERSON
THEY CALL HIJIRI.
IT TURNS OUT TO BE A SHIKIGAMI
CONTROLLED BY KIKYO.
>> THE REAL KIKYO
IS SUBMERGED UNDERWATER.
IS SHE ALIVE?
>> YOU MUST CHOOSE
WHETHER TO SAVE HER.
YOU ALONE CAN SAVE HER.
HER LIFE IS IN YOUR HANDS.
>> NEXT TIME, KAGOME'S
INSTINCTIVE CHOICE.
ONLY I CAN SAVE HER?
AND YOU WANT ME TO DECIDE?