- TIME'S UP.
- A LOT OF HELP
THAT WAS--
STUDYING WHEN I WAS
IN THE FEUDAL ERA.
MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE
LISTENED TO INUYASHA
AND NOT BOTHERED
TO COME BACK.
HUH?
- HOW DID IT GO?
- YOU DO OK?
- WORSE THAN AWFUL.
- HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
WAS THAT MATH TEST
A SNAP OR WHAT?
- WAS NOT!
- HA HA. OH!
- SO, KAGOME, TELL US
HOW THAT GUY OF YOURS
IS DOING THESE DAYS.
- HMM? GUY OF MINE?
- YEAH, YOU KNOW...
- MR. ATTITUDE.
- HE'S NOT THAT BAD.
- THE TWO-TIMING ONE.
- HE'S NOT ACTUALLY
TWO-TIMING.
- OK, THEN WHAT WOULD
YOU CALL HIM?
- UH...PLATONIC, I GUESS.
- HA HA. PLATONIC?
- SO HE'S A PLATONIC
TWO-TIMER?
- WOULD YOU STOP
TALKING LIKE THAT?
- KAGOME, LET ME GIVE YOU
A LITTLE PIECE OF ADVICE.
- YEAH? WHAT?
- HE'S NO GOOD FOR YOU.
- YEAH. YUKA'S RIGHT.
- WHAT'S WITH YOU GUYS?
- HE'S NO GOOD.
- TERRIBLE.
- HE IS?
- HMM? WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- HE'S SELFISH
AND RUDE, RIGHT?
- WELL, YEAH.
- AND NOT TO MENTION
JEALOUS.
WAIT. DOES HE KNOW
ABOUT HOJO?
- HMM...COME TO THINK OF IT,
MAYBE HE DOESN'T.
- IF HE DOESN'T KNOW
ABOUT HOJO,
THEN WHO IS HE
JEALOUS ABOUT?
- HMM...PROBABLY KOGA.
- UH! KOGA?
- AAH!
UH...THERE'S NOTHING
BETWEEN ME AND KOGA.
HONESTLY!
- THEN HOW COME
HE'S SO JEALOUS?
- UH...PROBABLY
BECAUSE...
WELL, KOGA SAID THAT
HE'S IN LOVE WITH ME.
[GASPS]
- YOU MEAN
YOU'RE TWO-TIMING, TOO?
- NO! IT'S NOTHING
LIKE THAT.
I DON'T FEEL
ANYTHING FOR KOGA.
I'M TOTALLY INDIFFERENT.
- THIS SURE IS A SHOCKER.
I HAD NO IDEA
YOU WERE SO POPULAR
OUTSIDE OF SCHOOL, KAGOME.
- I'M NOT POPULAR, OK?
KOGA LIKES ME.
END OF STORY.
- BUT HE TOLD YOU
HE LOVES YOU.
- OH, WOW. I WISH
SOMEBODY WOULD TELL ME
THAT HE'S
IN LOVE WITH ME.
[SIGHS]
- I AM IN LOVE
WITH YOU!
- YOU SURE ARE
LUCKY, KAGOME.
- I GUESS IT'S
KIND OF NICE BEING LOVED.
YOU KNOW, SOMEONE
EVEN ASKED ME
TO HAVE HIS CHILDREN
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
[GASPS]
- WHO ASKED YOU?
- WAS IT KOGA?
- OR THE TWO-TIMER?
- NOPE. IT WASN'T
EITHER OF THEM.
[GASPS]
- SO THERE'S
A THIRD GUY?
- YEAH, WHO IS IT?
- ONLY AN OLDER MAN
WOULD ASK SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- SURE, HE IS
OLDER THAN ME,
BUT I THINK HE'S IN LOVE
WITH SOMEBODY ELSE.
- YOU'RE HIS MISTRESS?
- DON'T GET INVOLVED!
- YOU'RE MAKING IT SOUND
LIKE A BIG DEAL.
HE GOES AROUND SAYING THAT
TO EVERY YOUNG WOMAN.
- YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
[SIGHS]
- I WANT YOU
TO HAVE MY CHILDREN.
[SCREAMING]
- IT MEANS NOTHING,
I SAID!
[SCREAMING STOPS]
- YEESH.
- OK, SO FAR, YOU'VE GOT
AT LEAST 3 GUYS.
SO, WHERE DO YOU MEET
ALL THESE MEN ANYWAY?
- YEAH. GOOD POINT.
YOUR MAIN GUY SEEMS
LIKE A DELINQUENT.
- AND THIS KOGA DUDE
SEEMS PRETTY PUSHY.
- HOJO DOESN'T EVEN
STAND A CHANCE.
- YOU SURE GO FOR THE STRONG
TYPE, DON'T YOU, KAGOME?
- IT'S NOT THAT.
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
- I JUST KNOW YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE MAN PROBLEMS.
- YEAH, NOT TO MENTION
AN UNHAPPY MARRIAGE.
- DON'T BE SO SILLY,
YOU GUYS.
- SO, HOW'S IT GOING
WITH DELINQUENT MAN THESE DAYS?
- HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THINGS GOING OK
WITH HIM?
- UH...I GUESS.
NOT BAD ANYWAY.
[SLURP]
- SO, IT'S GOING
ALL RIGHT, THEN?
- SHE MUST
REALLY LIKE HIM.
- COULD WE CHANGE
THE SUBJECT?
- WELL, EXCUSE US
FOR WORRYING.
- YOU SEEM TO HAVE
EVERYTHING UNDER CONTROL.
- IT'S WORKING OUT,
AND THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
[GIGGLES]
- WHAT?
- I WOULDN'T BE
SO SURE.
[DOG BARKING]
- I GOT AN 82
ON MY MATH TEST.
- GOOD JOB, DEAR.
YOU STUDIED HARD.
- LOOK, SIS!
I GOT AN 82!
- I HEARD! GOOD JOB!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING? AAH!
CUT IT OUT!
- YOU'D BETTER GET
A PERFECT SCORE NEXT TIME.
- YOU'RE CHOKING ME!
- OK, SETTLE DOWN.
TIME FOR DINNER, YOU TWO.
- ALL RIGHT.
- UH! OK.
- THANKS, MOM.
MMM!
YUMMY.
- YOU ARE EATING OVER
ON THE OTHER SIDE, AREN'T YOU?
- VEGGIES AND ROOTS
AND STUFF,
BUT NOTHING YUMMY
LIKE YOUR FOOD, MOM.
- THEN EAT UP
WHILE YOU'RE HERE, DEAR.
- WHEN ARE YOU
GOING BACK, KAGOME?
- MMM! WELL, MY TEST
IS OVER.
SO I PLAN TO GET
A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
THEN I'LL GO TO CLASS
AGAIN TOMORROW.
I'LL LEAVE AFTER THAT.
- SO, HOW DID YOU DO
ON YOUR TEST, ANYWAY?
- DON'T EVEN ASK.
- THAT'S NO SURPRISE.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT
ON YOUR PLATE, AS IT WERE.
- MMM! MMM-MMM!
YUM! THIS IS HEAVEN!
AH! ABSOLUTE HEAVEN!
AH! THIS IS THE LIFE.
HMM! MMM...
I WONDER
HOW EVERYONE'S DOING.
OH, WELL. I'M HAPPY.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- IT'S LONELY
WITHOUT KAGOME HERE.
- HMM. YOU THINK SO?
NOTHING'S DIFFERENT.
- YOU LIAR.
YOU'RE NOT KIDDING ANYONE.
YOU'VE BEEN IN A DAZE
SINCE SHE LEFT.
IT'S TOTALLY OBVIOUS
THAT YOU MISS HER.
OW! WHAT DID YOU
DO THAT FOR?
- WHEN DID KAGOME SAY
SHE'S RETURNING, INUYASHA?
- LET'S SEE.
1, 2, 3...TOMORROW.
- SHE'S GONNA
COME BACK TOMORROW?
WELL, THEN WE'D BETTER
GO BACK TO THE VILLAGE
AND BE THERE
TO GREET HER.
- YOU KNOW, WE'VE BEEN
ROAMING AROUND THE COUNTRYSIDE
WITHOUT ANY LUCK AT ALL.
- WITHOUT KAGOME
AROUND HERE,
WE CAN'T GET ANY LEADS
ON THE SACRED JEWEL.
- AND THERE'S BEEN NO SIGN
OF NARAKU EITHER.
- IF ONLY I COULD CATCH
A SCENT OF HIM.
I COULD GET
ON HIS TAIL NO PROBLEM.
- YOU WANT TO COME OUT?
THEN ALLOW ME
TO GRANT YOU YOUR WISH.
- WHO WAS THAT--
MY BROTHER?
- HE'S NOTHING
LIKE THE REST OF YOU.
LET'S GO.
- BOSS, WHICH VILLAGE
WILL WE HIT NEXT?
- SOMEPLACE WITH PLENTY
OF WOMEN AND DRINK.
- FINE PLAN.
- HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
- BOSS, COME OVER HERE!
- WHAT IS IT NOW?
WHAT IS THAT?
IS IT ALIVE?
THAT THING IS DISGUSTING.
LET'S KILL IT.
- RIGHT.
[MEN SHOUTING]
- AAH! A HAND!
[MEN GASP]
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
- JUST LOOK AT HIM.
HE HASN'T GOT A FACE.
[MEN SHOUTING]
- AAH!
[GROANING]
WHO AM I?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- INUYASHA, ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?
- NOBODY COULD MISTAKE
NARAKU'S DISGUSTING STENCH.
THIS WAY.
IT REEKS ALL OVER
OF NARAKU--
HIM AND THE SMELL
OF FRESH HUMAN BLOOD.
- DO YOU THINK
THEY'RE ALL DEAD?
- THEY'RE BANDITS.
HUH? WHAT THE HELL?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- COME AND TAKE
A LOOK AT THIS.
HIS FACE HAS
BEEN CARVED RIGHT OFF.
- THIS ONE, TOO.
- REALLY?
SO IS THIS ONE.
- EVERY LAST MAN
HAS HAD HIS FACE HACKED OFF.
- OOH! LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
- NARAKU'S BEHIND THIS.
- YEAH, BUT WHY WOULD HE
STEAL THEIR FACES? GRR!
- DEMON...ARE YOU
THE SOURCE OF EVIL?
- AH! MASTER MUSO,
THAT THING HAS NO FACE!
WHAT IS IT?
- STAY BACK
AND OUT OF DANGER.
- YES, MASTER.
- DEMON, WHERE
DO YOU COME FROM?
- WHERE, YOU ASK?
I DON'T KNOW.
- WHY HAVE YOU DONE
SUCH A CRUEL THING
TO ALL THOSE PEOPLE?
- GIVE ME YOUR FACE.
- YOU WANT A FACE? IS THAT
WHY YOU KILLED ALL THOSE PEOPLE?
YOU DESPICABLE SAVAGE!
- YOUR FACE!
- MASTER'S IN DANGER!
- YOU ARE NOTHING
BUT PURE EVIL. HYAH!
PERISH!
- GIVE ME YOUR--AAH!
- HE DID IT!
[GROWLING]
AAH!
- AAH!
[NEIGHS]
- NO!
- OH, YES.
I HAVE A NEW FACE...FINALLY.
[LAUGHING]
HELLO. NICE FACE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- GRR! IMPUDENCE!
MOVE, OR I'LL SLAY YOU.
- NOW THAT I HAVE
A FINE FACE,
NEXT I WILL NEED
A FINE WEAPON.
YOUR SWORD WILL DO NICELY.
DON'T YOU THINK SO?
[MAN GASPS]
OH, YES, INDEED.
IT'S A FINE SWORD, ALL RIGHT.
- WHO ARE YOU--A DEMON?
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
[BELL RINGING]
[VILLAGERS SHOUTING]
[EVIL LAUGHTER CONTINUES]
[CHUCKLES]
HMM...HA HA HA.
HMM...
- WHY?
IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
I WANT MORE...
MORE OF SOMETHING.
WHAT IS IT?
[HORSE NEIGHING]
HA HA HA. MAYBE THAT VILLAGE
WILL BE NEXT.
THAT VILLAGE...
STRANGE...THESE MEMORIES.
HA HA HA!
- YOU HOLD IT
RIGHT THERE!
- WHOA!
SPEAK. WHO ARE YOU?
- SOMEONE WHO'S BEEN OUT
LOOKING FOR YOU.
- BYE, YOU GUYS.
I'M OFF.
- SEE YOU LATER, SIS.
- BE CAREFUL, NOW.
- DO YOUR BEST, GIRL.
- IT NEVER CEASES
TO AMAZE ME.
- HOW COME SHE'S
THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN GO?
- IT'S HER FATE.
THAT'S THE ONLY EXPLANATION.
- HMM...
- OH, RIGHT.
I'D BETTER GO SHOPPING
SO I CAN STOCK UP ON FOOD
FOR HER WHEN SHE RETURNS.
- I'LL GO, TOO!
- AND SO SHALL I.
- WHERE'S NARAKU?
- NARAKU?
- DON'T PLAY INNOCENT.
YOU'RE ANOTHER ONE
OF HIS INCARNATIONS.
YOU REEK OF HIS STENCH.
- DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT ME AT ALL?
- COULD YOU TELL ME
WHO I AM, WHERE I'M FROM?
- SHUT UP!
- INUYASHA, I THINK
HE'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR ALL THE KILLINGS,
NOT NARAKU.
- ONE THING'S CERTAIN--
HE DEFINITELY HAS
THE SAME SMELL AS NARAKU.
- ARE YOU THE ONE
WHO KILLED THE BANDITS
AND STOLE THEIR FACES?
- YES, THAT WAS ME,
BUT THEY WERE ALL SO UGLY
THAT I COULDN'T USE THEM.
BUT THIS ONE
IS BEAUTIFUL.
- DID YOU STEAL
THAT FACE, TOO?
- YES. I WANTED TO HAVE
A HANDSOME FACE...
AND MONEY, WOMEN.
I WANTED IT ALL.
AND I STOLE EVERYTHING,
BUT IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
THERE'S
SOMETHING MISSING.
TELL ME, WHAT IS IT
THAT I'M CRAVING HERE?
- WHY, YOU...
- HE'S NOT JOKING.
- HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
WHO HE IS.
HE'S NOTHING LIKE NARAKU'S
OTHER INCARNATIONS.
- HA. EXCELLENT.
THEY FOUND EACH OTHER.
HE'S THE MOST ABOMINABLE
CREATION OF MY FLESH YET.
I'M SURE YOU'LL AGREE,
INUYASHA.
NOW, THEN...
- YOU WERE THE ONE
THAT ATTACKED THE VILLAGE
AND SET IT ABLAZE.
- YES, I DID. I THOUGHT THAT
IF I SLAUGHTERED SOME PEOPLE,
IT MIGHT HELP
RESTORE MY MEMORIES.
IT DIDN'T WORK, BUT I DID
HAVE MYSELF A GOOD TIME.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- I TOLD YOU,
I CAN'T RECALL.
OH, I KNOW. HOW ABOUT
CALLING ME MUSO?
YES, CALL ME MUSO.
THAT WILL DO QUITE NICELY.
IT'S THE NAME OF THE YOUNG MONK
WHO GAVE ME HIS FACE.
KIND OF HIM, WASN'T IT?
GAVE YOU HIS FACE?
YOU SLAUGHTERED THE POOR GUY!
- WHY ARE YOU
LOOKING AT ME LIKE THAT?
I DON'T LIKE IT.
- THE FEELING'S MUTUAL.
- YOU KNOW WHAT? I REALLY DON'T
LIKE THE LOOK OF YOUR FACE.
SAY, HAVE WE EVER
MET BEFORE?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT OBVIOUSLY,
THIS CONVERSATION
IS GOING NOWHERE FAST.
- INUYASHA, NO.
- SOMEONE WHO SMELLS
EXACTLY LIKE NARAKU
IS KILLING
INNOCENT PEOPLE.
HE DESERVES TO DIE!
- JUST TRY IT! GRR!
- HYAH!
DIE!
- HE DID IT!
- NOT YET.
- WHAT'S HIS BODY
MADE OF?
IT'S LIKE...
CLAY OR SOMETHING.
UH!
- NARAKU'S POISON INSECTS!
- HUH?
- AAH!
- HIS ARM'S BACK!
- HE'S ABSORBING THE POISON
INSECTS INTO HIS BODY.
MY WIND TUNNEL WILL BE
USELESS AGAINST HIM.
- I'M MORE AMAZING
THAN I THOUGHT I WAS.
SO, WHAT'S IN THAT VILLAGE
OVER THERE?
- HUH? WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- THAT VILLAGE
IS CALLING ME.
IF I SLAUGHTER
THE VILLAGERS,
MAYBE THIS TIME,
I'LL REMEMBER SOMETHING.
HYAH!
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
GRR!
- UH!
- WHAT?
- STAY BACK! AAH!
- NICE. THIS WILL DO
JUST FINE.
- AAH!
- HERE I COME!
- HMM! THERE!
- WE'VE GOT A FIGHT
ON OUR HANDS.
WE MUST USE
EXTREME CAUTION.
- YES, ESPECIALLY SINCE
HE'S NARAKU'S CREATION.
- I'LL BRING HIM DOWN!
HYAH!
[CHOKING]
- INUYASHA!
- HOW'S THAT?
- DAMN.
- INUYASHA!
- HUH? KAGOME'S COME BACK.
- INUYASHA.
- KAGOME!
- SORRY I'M LATE,
YOU GUYS.
- STAY BACK, KAGOME!
STAY BACK!
- AH!
THAT WOMAN.
WHAT WAS...THAT VISION?
- HE'S ONE OF NARAKU'S
INCARNATIONS.
STAY BACK
AND OUT OF DANGER.
- UH-HUH.
- THAT WOMAN...
WHO IS SHE?
- ARE YOU GONNA GAWK
OR FIGHT?
- YEAH! NOW YOU GOT HIM!
- THAT WOMAN...WHO IS SHE?
I KNOW HER.
UH! I REMEMBER!
I KNOW WHO SHE IS!
- YOU WON'T BE BABBLING
FOR MUCH LONGER. YOU'RE DEAD.
- OUT OF MY WAY! WOMAN!
- GOT HIM! UH!
- THAT WRETCHED DEMON!
- HA HA HA!
COME TO ME!
- RUN FOR IT!
- AAH! AH! OH!
- NO! KAGOME!
- KAGOME!
- HA HA HA!
YOU ARE THE ONE!
- WHO IS THIS GUY?
WHY ME? WHAT DOES HE WANT?
- IT IS THIS WOMAN
THAT I HAVE BEEN MISSING.
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
- HE TAKES US FOR FOOLS.
HE'S NARAKU'S INCARNATION,
YET HE CLAIMS
HE'S NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
- KAGRA TELLS INUYASHA
THAT MUSO IS IN THE CAVE,
WHERE 50 YEARS AGO,
KIKYO TENDED
TO THE BANDIT ONIGUMO.
- IT MIGHT BE A TRAP, BUT WE
SHOULD FIND SOME ANSWERS THERE.
- MEANWHILE, NARAKU SETS OUT
TO DESTROY KIKYO.
NEXT TIME, ONIGUMO'S
MEMORY RESTORED.
- I'LL GET REVENGE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED 50 YEARS AGO.