>> FOR THE FIRST TIME IN AGES,
I WENT HOME TO THE PRESENT.
WHILE I WAS TAKING PART IN THE
CULTURAL FESTIVAL, WE ENDED UP
HAVING TO SLAY SEVERAL DEMONS.
WAS I EVER BUSY!
A DEMON!
INUYA--I MEAN, PEKOPON!
DO SOMETHING!
>> I'M ALREADY ON IT.
WINDSCAR!
HAH!
HOW'S THAT?
>> FINALLY IT WAS TIME TO RETURN
TO THE FEUDAL ERA.
WE HAVE TO DO OUR BEST TO FIND
THE REMAINING SHARDS OF THE
SHIKON JEWEL.
[THUNDER]
>> FARWELL, FATHER.
FAREWELL, MOTHER.
TONIGHT I WILL HAVE TO
LEAVE YOU.
>> DON'T WORRY, DEAR.
WE ARE ALL GOING TO PROTECT YOU.
>> HOW COULD I LIVE WITH MYSELF
KNOWING I'D GIVEN MY DAUGHTER AS
A BRIDE TO A DEMON?
>> HERE HE COMES!
>> WHERE IS SHE?
[GASPING]
WHERE IS MY LOVELY BRIDE?
>> IT'S HERE!
[ROARS]
[SOBBING]
>> HOW LOVELY.
MY DEAR GIRL, WILL YOU BEAR
MY CHILDREN?
>> YES, MY MASTER.
>> HA HA!
EXCELLENT!
THEN COME, MY BRIDE.
[SNORTING LAUGHTER]
>> HMPH!
[BIRDS SINGING]
>> WHAT?
A DEMON WHO STEALS YOUNG GIRLS?
>> YES.
YOU SEE, OUR SHRINE WAS
DEMOLISHED BY A BAND OF DEMONS
THAT CAME FLYING PAST.
THE DEMON THAT HAD BEEN SEALED
INSIDE THE SHRINE WAS
ACCIDENTALLY SET FREE.
WHENEVER THE REVIVED DEMON SEES
A BEAUTIFUL YOUNG GIRL, HE ASKS
IF SHE WILL BEAR HIS CHILD,
AND THEN ABDUCTS HER.
>> HOW AWFUL.
>> HMPH!
DESPICABLE!
WANTING THEM TO GIVE BIRTH TO
HIS BABIES.
HOW DARE HE!
>> AS IF YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
>> THOSE VILLAGES THAT REFUSE TO
GIVE THE DEMON A BRIDE WERE
COMPLETELY DESTROYED.
>> WHAT A LOATHSOME BEING.
>> WE'D LOVE TO HELP YOU OUT,
OF COURSE, BUT I'M AFRAID WE
HAVE THE REMAINING JEWEL SHARDS
YET TO FIND.
OUR APOLOGIES.
>> WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE THEM
LIKE THIS.
THOSE DEMONS APPEARED BECAUSE OF
MOUNT HAKUREI, RIGHT?
>> IS THERE NO ONE WHO WILL
HELP THEM?
>> UH...
>> WELL, I GUESS IT'S UP TO ME
TO DO THE DIRTY WORK.
>> THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
>> I'LL TAKE CARE OF THE LITTLE
CRETIN AND BE BACK IN NO TIME.
>> I'M SURE IF INUYASHA GOES,
THERE'LL BE NO PROBLEMS AT ALL.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THE SOONER THE DEMON'S GONE,
THE BETTER.
OUR BEAUTIFUL MAIDENS CAN'T
STAY IN THE CAVES FOREVER.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> WE'VE GATHERED UP ALL THE
LOVELY GIRLS FROM THE
SURROUNDING AREAS AND PUT THEM
INTO A CAVE WHERE THE DEMON
CAN'T FIND THEM.
>> AHEM.
I'D BETTER GO, TOO.
'D WORRY IF INUYASHA WENT
BY HIMSELF.
>> SANGO, YOU'RE GOING ALONG,
TOO?
>> DEFINITELY.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT THE GIRLS,
TOO.
BUT NOT FOR THE REASON THAT
KISUKE MENTIONED.
>> HMM.
>> BYE, KAEDE!
BE BACK SOON!
>> HOW DID THEY ALL END UP
GOING?
>> THE DEMON HAS A CERTAIN TASTE
IN WOMEN.
HE ONLY GOES AFTER YOUNG,
UNMARRIED LADIES.
>> HMM.
YOUNG AND UNATTACHED.
INTERESTING.
>> WE HAVE TO STAY ON OUR TOES.
>> DON'T WORRY, MY EYES ARE
PEELED.
>> WHY IS SANGO ALL WORKED UP?
SOMETHING I SHOULD KNOW ABOUT?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW TOTALLY
CLUELESS YOU ARE SOMETIMES.
>> THERE IT IS.
THAT'S THE CAVE.
>> MASTER KISUKE?
LADIES, IT'S OK TO COME OUT.
KISUKE HAS RETURNED, AND HE'S
BROUGHT HELP.
[GIRLS CHATTERING]
>> MAN, WHAT'S GOT INTO THEM?
>> YOU CAN RELAX NOW, LADIES.
I'VE BROUGHT ALONG THESE EXPERT
DEMON-SLAYERS, AND THEY'LL TAKE
CARE OF EVERYTHING.
>> OH, THANK GOODNESS.
>> I WAS SO WORRIED.
>> YOU CAN TRUST THESE FOLKS
COMPLETELY, LADIES.
>> DEFINITELY.
EXCEPT FOR A COUPLE CHARACTER
FLAWS.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> I MEANT MIROKU.
>> AHEM.
GETTING STRAIGHT TO BUSINESS, I
CAME UP WITH A PLAN ON THE WAY
HERE, A STRATEGY TO KEEP THE
DEMON FROM CHOOSING YOU ALL
AS BRIDES.
>> IS THERE REALLY SUCH A WAY,
MONK?
>> THERE IS.
JUST ONE, THOUGH.
AS I UNDERSTAND IT, THE DEMON
ONLY CHOOSES YOUNG, UNMARRIED
WOMEN.
>> YES, THAT'S CORRECT.
>> THEREIN LIES THE CRUX.
MISS, WOULD YOU CONSIDER BEARING
MY CHILD?
DO SO, AND THE DEMON WILL SURELY
CEASE TO HAVE ANY INTEREST
IN YOU.
>> I SEE.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
>> MONK!
>> HMM?
>> IF THAT'S A JOKE, IT ISN'T
FUNNY!
>> HA HA HA!
[THUNDER]
>> DEMONIC AURA!
>> OH, NO, IT MUST BE HIM!
MAYBE HE FOUND THIS HIDING
PLACE!
>> INUYASHA.
>> WELL, WELL.
SO THAT'S THE DEMON I'VE BEEN
SENSING NEARBY.
IT STINKS LIKE A WILD BEAST.
>> MIROKU!
>> YOU WILL HURRY BACK TO ME,
WON'T YOU?
>> OF COURSE.
>> I'M SECOND IN LINE.
>> NOW, FOR A SAFE DELIVERY--
[THUD]
>> YOU KNOW, YOU GIRLS CAN'T
BELIEVE EVERYTHING YOU HEAR.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T LET THE GIRLS COME
OUTSIDE.
>> THAT DEMON WIELDS A HUGE
SPEAR, AND HE'S VERY FIERCE.
>> DYING TO GET A LOOK AT THE
CREEP.
>> HEY, WAIT FOR US!
>> LET'S GET TO HIM BEFORE HE
GETS TO US, SO HE DOESN'T GET
CLOSE TO THE GIRLS' CAVE.
>> WILL THE LADIES BE SAFE?
AFTER ALL, IF HE'S A BEAST, HE
SHOULD BE ABLE TO SNIFF THE
LADIES OUT.
>> IN THAT CASE, HE'LL BE DRAWN
BY THE SMELL OF KAGOME.
>> I KNOW THE DEMON ONLY GOES
FOR YOUNG, PRETTY GIRLS, BUT
THERE'S NO WAY YOU'RE USING ME
FOR BAIT.
>> YOUNG AND PRETTY?
I DON'T SEE ANYONE LIKE THAT
AROUND HERE.
>> HMM.
SIT!
>> AAH!
>> HE WILL NEVER LEARN.
>> [GROWLS]
[SNORTING LAUGHTER]
>> HAVE YOU GIVEN UP AND BROUGHT
ME A BRIDE?
>> THAT MUST BE HIM.
HUH?
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> CHATTERING
>> [CHUCKLING]
>> UH, YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO BE
THE DEMON WHO'S LOOKING FOR
WIVES, WOULD YOU?
>> CORRECT.
YOUNG LADY, WOULD YOU LIKE TO
BEAR MY CHILD?
>> I THINK I'VE HEARD THAT
SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
>> OH, MAN.
>> HUH?
>> GEEZ, WHAT A LETDOWN.
>> WHO ARE YOU AND WHAT DO YOU
WANT?
>> FROM ALL THE TALK, I WAS
EXPECTING A WAY TOUGHER DEMON.
AND KIND OF HOPING I COULD GET A
BIT OF A WORKOUT FIGHTING HIM.
>> AND WE GET A PIG-DEMON.
>> I RESENT THAT!
I AM NO PIG, I'M A WILD BOAR!
>> WELL, CLEARLY I DIDN'T NEED
TO COME ALONG.
INUYASHA, YOU HANDLE IT.
>> HEY, GUYS, DO WHAT YOU LIKE
WITH THE PIG.
>> SANGO, TAKE CARE OF HIM,
WOULD YOU?
>> UNH!
HEY, YOU TWO!
>> YES?
>> HAH!
LOOK AT THEM, FEARING MY POWER
AND RUNNING OFF WITH THEIR TAILS
BETWEEN THEIR LEGS.
>> YOU WISH.
>> HUH?
>> THEY LEFT BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T
LOOK WORTH THE FUSS.
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> AAH!
>> HOW DARE YOU UNDERESTIMATE
THE POWER OF CHOKYUKAI.
>> CHOKYUKAI?
HAVEN'T I HEARD THAT NAME
SOMEWHERE BEFORE?
OR AM I JUST IMAGINING IT?
>> WAIT, DON'T TELL ME YOU KNOW
THE GUY.
>> I LIKE PORK CHOPS FINE, BUT
I DON'T HANG OUT WITH PIGS.
YUCK!
>> I AM NOT A PIG, I'M A BOAR!
PERHAPS THIS WILL ASTONISH YOU.
THIS FELLOW HERE IS A DESCENDANT
OF SHAGOYJO, THE GREAT WATER
DEMON.
>> [SQUAWK]
>> HERE WE HAVE A DESCENDANT OF
THE HEAVENLY SAINT, SONGOKO.
>> [CHATTERS]
>> AND I AM CHOKYUKAI, DESCENDED
FROM CHOHAKKAI, THE GENERAL OF
THE ARMY OF HEAVEN!
>> HUH?
>> WELL, WELL, ARE YOU TOO
IMPRESSED EVEN TO SPEAK?
I'VE TAKEN A LESSON FROM MY
ANCESTOR CHOHAKKAI AND DECIDED
TO MARRY HUMAN GIRLS.
>> WHAT'S THE SWINE TALKING
ABOUT?
>> GAH!
YOU'VE NEVER HEARD OF
"THE JOURNEY TO THE WEST"?
>> OH!
SO YOU ACTUALLY ARE DESCENDED
FROM CHOHAKKAI IN "THE JOURNEY
TO THE WEST"?
>> DO YOU KNOW THAT?
>> NOPE, IT'S NEWS TO ME.
>> I HAVE NO CLUE WHAT HE'S
TALKING ABOUT.
IT FIGURES KAGOME WOULD KNOW,
THOUGH.
>> SO, YOUNG MISS, IT SEEMS THAT
YOU HAVE HEARD OF MY ANCESTOR.
>> "THE JOURNEY TO THE WEST" IS
A FAMOUS CHINESE EPIC TALE OF
THE MONK SANZO WHO MAKES FRIENDS
WITH 3 DEMONS: A MONKEY, A WATER
SPRITE, AND A PIG.
AND TOGETHER THEY GO TO INDIA TO
RETRIEVE THE HOLY SUTRAS.
>> OH, SO YOU DO KNOW THIS GUY.
>> I LIKE PORK AS MUCH AS THE
NEXT GIRL, BUT I DON'T KNOW
ANY PIGS!
>> HAH!
YOU KNOW ALL ABOUT MY ANCESTOR!
WHAT AN EXCEPTIONAL GIRL
YOU ARE.
THIS IS YOUR LUCKY DAY.
I THINK I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU
MY WIFE!
>> NO WAY.
>> HA HA HA, I'VE HEARD THAT
BEFORE.
WHEN A GIRL SAYS "NO," SHE
USUALLY MEANS "YES."
>> I LIKE PORK ROAST, BUT NO,
THANK YOU.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THESE TWO
ARE TALKING ABOUT.
>> HA HA HA!
YOU CAN'T RESIST THIS.
>> AAH!
>> HEY, WATCH OUT!
AAH!
HUH?
>> UNH!
INUYASHA!
>> IS IT ME, OR IS INUYASHA
ACTING WEIRD?
>> INUYASHA!
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
>> [GIGGLES]
MASTER...
>> HUH?
OH, MAN, I'VE NEVER SEEN THIS
SIDE OF YOU BEFORE.
>> THIS COULD ONLY END WITH
A BROKEN HEART!
>> SOMETHING'S FUNNY ABOUT THAT
GOLDEN TIARA.
>> UNH!
>> IT'S TIGHT!
>> KEEP PULLING!
>> UNH!
HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
>> YOU NEARLY VOLUNTEERED TO
BECOME CHOKYUKAI'S WIFE, THAT'S
WHAT HAPPENED.
>> [GAGS]
>> WHEN PLACED UPON A GIRL'S
HEAD, THIS TIARA HAS THE POWER
TO MAKE HER FALL IN LOVE WITH
ITS MASTER.
IF I PLACE THIS ON A GIRL'S
HEAD, I CAN MAKE HER FALL MADLY
IN LOVE WITH ME!
>> NO!
HOW CAN YOU EVEN THINK THAT?
IDIOT!
HUH?
>> OHH...
OH, MASTER.
>> HUH?
>> LOOK AT THAT.
DOESN'T IT MAKE THE WEARER FALL
IN LOVE WITH THE ONE THAT
PLACED IT?
>> I'M PRETTY SURE THAT ANYONE
WEARING IT FALLS IN LOVE WITH
CHOKYUKAI.
WITH NOBODY BUT HIM.
>> WAIT, MIROKU!
>> ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH FUN FOR
ONE DAY.
>> HUH?
>> AH!
>> NOW, MY BRIDE, LET US BE ON
OUR WAY.
>> YES, RIGHT AWAY, MASTER.
>> OVER MY DEAD BODY!
>> HA HA HA!
YOU WON'T INTERFERE!
HAH!
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME?
>> HA HA HA!
>> OH, MASTER.
>> DAMN YOU, PIG!
>> YOU STILL WANT TO INTERFERE?
SONGOKO!
SHAGOYJO!
ATTACK!
>> YAH!
[GROWLING]
[SNAPS]
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> WELL, WELL, THE MONGREL'S NOT
TOO BAD, I'LL GIVE HIM THAT
MUCH.
>> YOU KNOW, I'VE HAD JUST ABOUT
ENOUGH OF YOU JOKERS.
I'LL KNOCK YOU ALL BACK TO THE
CONTINENT!
>> TIME FOR YOU TO FEAR MY
POWER, AND RUN OFF WITH YOUR
TAIL BETWEEN YOUR LEGS.
>> SHUT UP, PIG-DEMON!
>> [ROARS]
I TOLD YOU, I'M A BOAR!
I'LL BEAT YOU TO A PULP!
>> JUST YOU TRY IT.
>> GOOD LUCK, MY DEAREST
HUSBAND.
>> KAGOME!
UNH!
>> NOW YOU DIE!
>> INUYASHA!
>> NOW THAT I HAVE MY BRIDE,
THERE'S NO REASON TO STAY.
SHALL WE, DEAR?
>> YES, BY ALL MEANS.
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
>> [SNORTING LAUGHTER]
>> DAMN IT!
KAGOME!
>> WELCOME HOME, MASTER.
WELCOME HOME.
>> HA HA HA!
I'VE BROUGHT YOU ALL A NEW
COMPANION.
YOU'LL SIT AT THE HEAD OF
THE TABLE.
IT SEEMS ONLY FITTING, MY
DEAREST WIFE.
>> YES, MY MASTER.
>> UNH!
>> INUYASHA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> DAMN IT.
I CAN'T TAKE IT!
ABOUT NOW, KAGOME IS...
>> [GIGGLING]
OH, MASTER.
>> I WAS SO CLUELESS!
>> THIS IS NO TIME TO GET ALL
UPSET ABOUT IT.
>> SHE'S RIGHT.
JUDGING FROM WHAT WE'VE HEARD,
THAT DEMON IS FROM THE
CONTINENT.
IT'S QUITE POSSIBLE THAT OUR
USUAL METHODS OF ERADICATION
WON'T WORK ON HIM.
FORTUNATELY, I HAVE A CHINESE
SUTRA WITH PRAYERS WRITTEN ON IT
IN THEIR LANGUAGE.
WE COULD TRY USING THIS.
IT MIGHT DO THE TRICK.
>> POSSIBLY, BUT HOW ARE WE
GOING TO FIND HIS LAIR?
>> EASY.
WE'LL JUST FOLLOW HIS SCENT.
HE'S GOT KAGOME WITH HIM,
THOUGH, SO WE CAN'T BE TOO
AGGRESSIVE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> I HAVE A PLAN THAT JUST
MIGHT WORK.
SHIPPO, COME LISTEN TO THIS.
[WHISPERING]
>> HEY, YEAH, THAT'S A GREAT
IDEA, MIROKU.
I HADN'T THOUGHT OF THAT.
>> WE'LL NEED EVERYONE TO WORK
TOGETHER.
>> AND I'VE GOT TO MAKE SURE NOT
TO LET YOU GUYS DOWN.
>> HA HA HA!
WHAT A FINE NIGHT THIS IS.
AHH!
WIVES, SOMEONE DANCE FOR ME, AND
MAKE IT GOOD.
HA HA HA!
>> EXCUSE ME!
>> HMM?
>> IS THERE ANYONE HOME?
>> A FEMALE VOICE, LIKE THE
TINKLING OF BELLS!
HOW CAN I HELP YOU, TRAVELING
WOMAN?
>> I'VE LOST MY WAY, AND I'M
IN TROUBLE.
COULD I BOTHER YOU TO PUT ME UP
FOR THE NIGHT, KIND SIR?
>> STAY ONE NIGHT, OR EVEN
1,000!
UNH!
DON'T BE COY, SHOW ME YOUR FACE.
>> BUT I AM SO SHY.
>> OH, MAN, THIS IS HOPELESS.
>> YOU'RE JUST MY TYPE.
WILL YOU BEAR MY CHILD?
>> OH, REALLY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE HE HASN'T
NOTICED.
>> EITHER THAT OR HE HAS VERY
STRANGE TASTE.
>> KAGOME!
>> COME, MAKE YOURSELF
COMFORTABLE.
WE CAN TALK INSIDE.
AFTER YOU, MY LOVELY.
>> HURRY UP, INUYASHA!
>> WHAT'S WRONG, MY PRECIOUS
ONE, ARE YOU TREMBLING WITH JOY?
FINE, THEN I'LL TREMBLE WITH
YOU.
HA HA HA!
>> I CAN'T TAKE THIS MUCH
LONGER.
THAT'S IT!
>> WHAT'S THIS?
HEY, I KNOW YOU!
YOU WERE WITH THAT DOG EARLIER!
>> SNAP OUT OF IT, KAGOME!
>> HUH?
INUYASHA!
>> HERE YOU GO.
YOU FORGOT SOMETHING.
>> YOU WRETCHES, YOU TRICKED ME.
>> YOUR TURN!
AAH!
>> GOOD JOB, SHIPPO!
>> I WON'T LET YOU TAKE MY
BRIDE AWAY.
RAH!
[SNORTING LAUGHTER]
>> OK, INUYASHA, NOW!
GIVE THAT SUTRA TO KAGOME!
>> HERE!
THIS IS A SUTRA FROM THE
CONTINENT.
ATTACH IT TO YOUR ARROW AND
FIRE IT!
>> GOTCHA!
>> UNH!
>> HAH!
I'VE GOTTA SAY, THAT'S NOT A BAD
PIKE FOR A PIG TO BE WIELDING.
>> YOU AIN'T SEEN NOTHING YET,
BELIEVE ME.
>> SO IT'S A TEST OF STRENGTH
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR, IS IT?
>> [SNIFFS]
WHAT'S THIS I'M SENSING?
WHAT?!
OH, NO, NOT THAT!
ANYTHING BUT THAT!
>> MAYBE THIS WILL TEACH YOU FOR
TOYING WITH A WOMAN'S EMOTIONS!
>> OH, NO!!
[YELLING]
>> THAT'S HARSH.
[YELLING FADES AWAY]
[OWL HOOTING]
>> MY ONLY REGRET IS THAT I LET
THAT SWINE GET AWAY.
AT LEAST HE WON'T BE CAUSING ANY
MORE TROUBLE AROUND HERE.
>> I'M SURE GLAD WE WERE ABLE TO
RESCUE EVERYONE.
>> YES, WE ARE, TOO.
AREN'T WE, MIRO--
HMM?
>> LADIES, WOULD YOU BEAR
MY CHILDREN?
>> THE MONK IS STARTING TO SOUND
JUST LIKE THAT DEMON.
>> NO KIDDING.
DO YOU THINK HE'S A DEMON, TOO?
>> ME, A DEMON?!
HELP ME OUT HERE, SANGO.
>> HMPH!
WHATEVER.
>> HELLO, LADIES!
IS EVERYONE ALL RIGHT?
>> HEY, LOOK, IT'S KISUKE.
[WOMEN EXCLAIMING]
>> OHH...
>> GUESS WE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT MIROKU, SEEING AS HE'S NOT
TOO POPULAR.
RIGHT?
>> [MEWS]
>> IT WAS SO FRIGHTENING.
>> THANK YOU, KISUKE.
>> THE PIG-DEMON WAS SO
DISGUSTING.
>> YES, BUT SO WAS THAT MONK.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> LITTLE BABY FOXES LOOK UP
TO SHIPPO AS THEIR MASTER.
>> WHO ARE YOU GUYS?
>> WE'VE COME TO TRAIN UNDER
YOU, MASTER SHIPPO.
PLEASE, MASTER, TRAIN US TO
BECOME AS STRONG AS YOU.
>> YOU HAVE SPECIAL TECHNIQUES,
RIGHT?
>> YOU MEAN MY FOX MAGIC,
"SMASHING TALL"?
>> SOMETHING MORE INCREDIBLE.
>> INCREDIBLE?
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT MOVE OF
INUYASHA'S, DO YOU?
>> NEXT TIME, "SHIPPO'S NEW
TECHNIQUE, THE HEART SCAR!"
>> THIS IS MY TRAGIC LOVE STORY,
A LOVE ABANDONED FOR COMBAT.