- LOOKS LIKE THE VILLAGE
WHERE I LIVED WITH FATHER.
- COME ON, SHIPPO.
LET'S GO.
- COMING.
- I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
THE KIND OF PLACE
WE'D FIND A JEWEL SHARD.
- HOW ABOUT IT?
ARE YOU SENSING A SHARD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
HERE, KAGOME?
- NO.
NOT AT ALL.
- WELL, I GUESS
WE MIGHT AS WELL SPLIT UP
AND SEE WHAT WE CAN FIND.
SEE YOU LATER.
- HUH?
HMM.
- YES?
WHAT IS IT?
- SO, CONVINCE ME THAT
YOU'RE NOT GOING WOMANIZING.
WILL YOU, MONK?
[LAUGHS]
- LOOK!
THE SIGN OF A DEMON PRESENCE!
- HUH?
HEY, COME BACK HERE.
HOW CAN YOU BE SO CALLOUS?
- UH, WHAT'S WITH YOU?
- WHERE YOU GOING, INUYASHA?
WE HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED
LOOKING YET.
- IF THERE WAS A DEMON AROUND,
I'D SMELL HIM.
- SURE THING, SLACKER.
AHH.
WHAT A GORGEOUS DAY.
WAIT.
I WONDER WHERE SHIPPO WENT.
- I DON'T KNOW.
WHO KNOWS.
PROBABLY WENT OFF TO PLAY.
HE'S JUST A KID, REMEMBER.
[CHILDREN SHOUTING]
- COME BACK HERE!
- ONE DAY THEY'LL APPRECIATE
WHAT I DO FOR THEM.
[PANTING]
- WE'VE BEEN IN A LOT
OF BATTLES LATELY.
KAGOME AND INUYASHA
COULD PROBABLY USE
SOME TIME ALONE.
[YAWNING]
UHH.
- HEY, YOU, STOP!
- HEY, GRAB HIM!
- GRAB HIM!
- STOP RUNNING!
- GET HER!
- QUIT IT!
[YELLING AND LAUGHTER]
- SATSUKI, YOU STOLE THE DRY
PERSIMMONS FROM MY HOUSE.
- YOU CAN'T PROVE THAT I DID IT.
- YOU'RE A THIEF.
- UHH.
- YOU'LL BE SORRY, 'CAUSE WHEN
MY BROTHER COMES HOME,
YOU'RE ALL GONNA GET IT.
- RIGHT.
EXCEPT THAT YOUR BROTHER DIED
A LONG TIME AGO
IN THE CIVIL WAR.
- MY PA WAS RIGHT THERE WITH HIM
WHEN HE WAS SLAIN.
- MY BROTHER ISN'T DEAD!
[SCREAMING]
- GET OFF HIM!
[YELLING]
YOU LYING THIEF!
- YOU'RE LYING!
- HUH?
- YOU WRETCHED SCOUNDRELS!
[SCREAMING]
- RUN, YOU GUYS!
[INDISTINCT]
[GRUNTING]
- HUH?
- SURE SHOWED THEM.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU'LL BE SAFE NOW.
- THANK YOU, LITTLE RACCOON.
- I'M A FOX.
- WELL, THANKS A LOT
FOR YOUR HELP.
DO YOU WANT SOME?
- HUH?
- IT'S THE PERSIMMON
THAT I TOOK.
YOU'LL LIKE IT.
- TERRIFIC.
I SAVED A THIEF.
- YOU'RE STRONG
FOR A LITTLE GUY.
I'M SATSUKI.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
[GULPS]
- UM, MY NAME IS SHIPPO.
- SHIPPO?
THAT'S A REALLY NICE NAME.
- MY FATHER GAVE IT TO ME.
- IS YOUR FATHER
A DEMON RACCOON, TOO?
- NO.
A FOX.
- JUST TEASING.
[LAUGHTER]
- SATSUKI, SO DON'T YOU
HAVE ANY PARENTS?
- THEY PASSED AWAY YEARS AGO.
- TOO BAD.
- IT'S OK, BECAUSE I STILL HAVE
A BIG BROTHER.
HE'S GONNA PROVE HIMSELF
IN THE WAR
AND BECOME A SAMURAI.
THEN HE'S COMING BACK FOR ME.
- HUH?
SO WERE THOSE BOYS
LYING TO YOU BEFORE THEN?
YOUR BROTHER DIDN'T DIE?
- HE'S GONNA COME BACK HOME.
EVEN IF HE IS DEAD,
HE'LL COME BACK TO LIFE.
- UH...
- HEY, I'LL SHOW YOU SOMETHING
THAT I'VE NEVER SHOWN
TO ANYONE BEFORE.
IT'S MY TREASURE,
AND IT CAN MAKE
ANY WISH COME TRUE.
ISN'T IT PRETTY?
IT'S A SHIKON JEWEL SHARD,
A PRECIOUS GEM SOUGHT BY DEMONS.
- IT'S THE SACRED JEWEL!
- WHAT IS THIS?
- IT'S A SACRED JEWEL SHARD,
AND IT WILL GRANT ANY WISH.
I'LL BECOME A SAMURAI.
I PROMISE.
- UH-HUH.
[CHUCKLES]
MY BROTHER WOULD NEVER
LIE TO ME.
- HMM.
[BIRDS CAWING]
- ARE YOU CERTAIN, MONK?
IS MY HOME INDEED
POSSESSED BY A DEMON?
- YES.
AND WE MUST
EXORCISE IT IMMEDIATELY.
THIS IS MY DUTY
AS A MAN OF THE CLOTH.
I EXPECT NO PAYMENT, HEADMAN.
- ABSURD.
YOU SHALL ALL BE GIVEN
A MEAL AND A BED TONIGHT.
- LOOK AT THAT GUY,
LYING THROUGH HIS TEETH AGAIN.
- SHH.
- HMM?
HMM.
[GIGGLES]
- UHH.
WHAT?
- SHH.
- HMM.
[THUMPING]
- EARTHQUAKE?
[SIGHS]
[GROWLING]
[GASPING]
- YOU MEAN THERE WAS A DEMON?
- SO YOU DIDN'T JUST MAKE IT UP?
- THERE'S A FIRST
FOR EVERYTHING.
PARDON ME?
[PANTING]
- YOU GUYS!
- HMM?
- KAGOME!
- YOU FOUND US.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
THAT WE WERE HERE?
- I FIGURED MIROKU
WOULDN'T WASTE
ANY TIME EXORCISING
THE WEALTHIEST-LOOKING HOUSE
IN THE VILLAGE.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
- YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT!
I FOUND A SHARD OF THE JEWEL!
[GASPS]
- SHE HAS IT?
- HMM?
- IF IT ISN'T SATSUKI.
- LISTEN, SATSUKI.
DO YOU THINK I COULD
TAKE A QUICK LOOK
AT THAT JEWEL SHARD OF YOURS?
- YOU WON'T STEAL IT, WILL YOU?
- SURE, WE WILL,
IF THE JEWEL SHARD'S REAL.
- INUYASHA, SIT, BOY.
- UHH!
DON'T WORRY.
I JUST WANT TO TAKE
A LOOK AT IT.
[GASPS]
- OH, NO!
IF IT IS REAL,
WE'LL HAVE TO TAKE IT FROM HER!
THEN SATSUKI'S WISH
WON'T COME TRUE!
AAH!
OH, STUPID ME!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
STUPID!
HOW COULD I HAVE BEEN SO STUPID!
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE
HOW STUPID I CAN BE!
- KAGOME?
- HUH?
- THAT'S ENOUGH NOW.
I'M GONNA GO HOME.
- THANKS FOR SHOWING IT TO US.
- UH, YOU'RE GONNA LET HER GO?
- SATSUKI, WON'T YOU CONSIDER
COMING TO LIVE WITH US?
- NO, THANKS.
MY BROTHER WILL COME FOR ME
ANY DAY NOW.
- UHH.
KAGOME, WHAT ABOUT THE SHARD?
- WELL, SHIPPO,
THAT WAS JUST A STONE FLOWER.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- CALLED QUARTZ, TO BE EXACT.
IT'S ONLY A COMMON ROCK
FOUND IN THE MOUNTAINS.
IT'S NOT A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
- IT'S JUST A FAKE.
[SIGHS]
POOR SATSUKI.
- SUCH A PITIFUL CHILD.
HER BROTHER TRULY HAS PASSED ON,
BUT SATSUKI REFUSES
TO BELIEVE IT.
- HOW SAD.
- PLEASE, SHARD.
BRING MY BROTHER
BACK HOME TO ME.
- I'VE TOLD HER
TO COME LIVE WITH US,
BUT SHE WON'T MOVE FROM THE HUT
SHE SHARED WITH HER BROTHER.
- I MAY HAVE BEEN DRIVEN
FROM THE HEADMAN'S RESIDENCE,
BUT I'LL HAVE MY RETALIATION.
I'LL USE THE GIRL.
- THE SACRED JEWEL HAS THE POWER
TO CREATE NARAKU'S INCARNATIONS.
IF A WISH WERE MADE
ON A REAL SHARD,
WOULD SATSUKI'S BROTHER
COME BACK TO LIFE
AND RETURN HOME?
HUH?
[MOANING]
[PANTING]
[SCREAMING]
[MOANING]
- I CAN'T STAND GEOMETRY.
- HMM.
FORGIVE ME, KAGOME.
[GRUNTING]
- HEY.
- OH, INUYASHA,
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
FAST ASLEEP BY NOW.
LET ME TAKE IT!
I NEED TO HELP SOMEONE!
COME ON!
- OH, DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
SHIPPO, YOU KNOW HOW POWERFUL
ONE SHARD OF
THE SACRED JEWEL IS.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU GO AROUND
GIVING TO HUMANS.
BESIDES, WHY ALL THE SUDDEN NEED
TO HELP THAT
NEW FRIEND OF YOURS?
- HE'S INFATUATED, OBVIOUSLY,
AND SHE WAS FAIRLY ATTRACTIVE,
I MUST ADMIT.
- SO THAT'S WHAT
THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
- YOU'RE ONE TO CRITICIZE!
SURE, I MAY HAVE FALLEN FOR HER,
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU
DARTING BACK AND FORTH
BETWEEN KIKYO AND KAGOME?
[MOANING]
- GET TO SLEEP.
- I'M SORRY.
[DOOR OPENS]
[GASPS]
- SATSUKI,
I'VE FINALLY RETURNED.
[GASPS]
- IS IT REALLY YOU?
- YES, IT IS.
YOU'VE WAITED SO LONG.
- MY BROTHER!
I KNEW YOU'D COME.
I JUST KNEW IT.
[SOBBING]
NO ONE ELSE BELIEVED IT,
BUT I DID.
- WELL, AT THE VERY LEAST,
I SHOULD SAY GOOD-BYE TO HER.
POOR SATSUKI.
I WONDER IF SHE'LL CONTINUE
TO WISH ON THAT FAKE SHARD.
[SIGHS]
I DON'T HAVE THE HEART.
I CAN'T TELL HER THE TRUTH.
- SHIPPO!
- SATSUKI?
- MY WISH CAME TRUE!
MY BROTHER FINALLY
CAME HOME TO ME!
- HUH?
- INUYASHA, WHERE'D SHIPPO
GET TO?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE HE'S WITH
THAT NEW FRIEND OF HIS
OR SOMETHING.
- YES.
HE WAS VERY WORRIED ABOUT HER.
- POOR GIRL.
HER BROTHER IS DEAD,
BUT SHE ACTUALLY BELIEVES THAT
THE STONE WILL BRING HIM
BACK TO HER AGAIN.
I'M GOING TO FIND THEM.
- ARE YOU BUTTING IN AGAIN?
- WAIT FOR ME, KAGOME.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
- SEE?
HE'S INJURED, BUT AT LEAST
HE'S BACK HERE WITH ME.
- SATSUKI, THANK YOU.
YOU AND THE SHARD
GUIDED ME HOME.
- HMM?
AAH!
A DEMON!
- YOU REST.
WE GOT SO MUCH CATCHING UP TO DO
AFTER YOU'RE BETTER.
- AYE.
YOU'VE HAD TO SUFFER
SO LONG WITHOUT ME,
BUT I PROMISE
TO MAKE IT ALL UP TO YOU.
[LAUGHS]
- SATSUKI.
- HMM?
- WE NEED TO TALK.
- YOU'RE NEW AROUND HERE,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU MUST BE WITH THE GROUP
THAT'S STAYING OVER
AT THE HEADMAN'S HOUSE.
- COME HERE, SATSUKI!
HURRY!
- SHIPPO?
- I NEED YOU TO BRING ME
SOMETHING NOW.
A REAL SHARD OF THE JEWEL.
- LET GO OF SATSUKI!
AAH!
- OH!
WHY DID YOU STRIKE MY FRIEND?
LOOK, I HAVE A SHARD
OF THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL
RIGHT HERE.
- CAN'T YOU TELL
BY LOOKING AT IT?
IT'S A PIECE OF RUBBISH.
COMPLETELY USELESS SCRAP.
[GASPS]
- HE CRUSHED SATSUKI'S
PRECIOUS WISHING STONE.
[GRUNTING]
- MOVE, BOY.
GET ME A SHARD OF THE JEWEL.
DO IT, OR I'LL HAVE
TO BREAK SATSUKI'S NECK.
- YOU IMPOSTOR!
WHO ARE YOU?
[LAUGHS]
- YOUR BROTHER.
WHO ELSE WOULD I BE?
[LAUGHS]
- SHOW YOURSELF, DEMON!
FALSE MAGIC!
[GASPS]
[LAUGHS]
- THAT WASN'T NICE AT ALL.
YOU COULD HAVE AT LEAST LET HER
THINK THAT I WAS HER BROTHER.
[GRUNTING]
- SATSUKI!
NOBODY MESSES WITH MY FRIENDS!
[GRUNTS]
COME ON!
HURRY!
- OK.
[GRUNTING]
- HUH?
HUH?
[INDISTINCT]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SCREAMS]
- HE MUST BE ON TO MY TRICK.
- YOU WON'T ESCAPE.
[GRUNTING]
- THIS'LL WORK.
I'LL KEEP HIM BUSY
WHILE YOU ESCAPE.
- NO.
I WON'T LEAVE YOU BEHIND.
- THE HORSE CAN ONLY TAKE ONE.
- SHIPPO!
- HMM.
HMM?
- I HAVE YOU NOW.
- IS THIS SATSUKI'S HUT?
LOOK.
A DEMON WITH A HUGE TORSO
MUST HAVE DONE ALL OF THIS.
- WHATEVER IT WAS,
IT SEEMS TO HAVE FLED.
- LET'S MOVE, MIROKU.
WE'VE GOTTA FIND SHIPPO.
- YES.
THE TWO OF THEM
HAD BETTER BE SAFE.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- LOOK AT THAT HORSE.
IT'S SHIPPO'S FOX MAGIC.
- THAT'S SATSUKI.
AAH!
[GASPS]
[SCREAMING]
- NICE CATCH, KIRARA.
- A DEMON IS AFTER SHIPPO.
- YES.
WE KNOW.
BETTER HURRY, KAGOME.
- MM-HMM.
[GRUNTING]
- I HOPE YOU'RE SAFE, SATSUKI.
- UHH!
UHH.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[LAUGHS]
- THE GIRL ESCAPED,
BUT NO MATTER TO ME.
IT WAS YOU WHO I DESIRE.
I'LL HOLD YOU HOSTAGE
TO GET A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
- IF YOU WANTED ME,
WHY DIDN'T YOU COME AFTER ME
FROM THE START?
YOU WENT OUT OF YOUR WAY
TO CRUSH SATSUKI'S HOPES,
AND NOW I'LL MAKE YOU
REGRET IT, DEMON.
- SHALL I PRESUME
YOU WISH TO TAKE ME ON?
- YOU BET, UGLY!
- STOMACH ACID.
- [INDISTINCT]
BOMBS AWAY!
NOW'S MY CHANCE.
[GRUNTING]
- YOU PEST,
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
- MAYBE I'M JUST NOT
STRONG ENOUGH TO DEFEAT HIM.
DON'T I HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO FIGHT LIKE MY FRIENDS DO?
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
- PLAYTIME'S OVER.
HUH?
SO YOU HAVE GONE
AND TRANSFORMED YOURSELF
INTO SOMETHING ELSE
YET AGAIN, HAVE YOU?
- WHAT?
YOU HAVE SOME KIND
OF GRUDGE AGAINST ME?
FINE BY ME.
I'LL TRY OUT MY NEW
BACKLASH WAVE.
- AND NOW WHAT KIND
OF TRICK IS IT
THAT YOU'RE TRYING TO PULL?
HUH?
- THIS MOVE USES THE WINDSCAR
TO SURROUND THE DEMON'S ENERGY
AND SEND IT FLYING
RIGHT BACK AT HIM.
BACKLASH!
HUH?
- HUH?
- OH, GREAT.
THIS LIZARD'S DEMON ENERGY
IS SO WEAK,
MY BACKLASH WAVE IS USELESS.
- IS THIS A DEBATE OR A BATTLE?
- IT WOULD BE A BATTLE
IF YOU WEREN'T SO WEAK.
[SQUEALS]
- HMM?
THIS IS THE VERY SAME DEMON
THAT I EXORCISED FROM
THE HEADMAN'S HOUSE LAST NIGHT.
[WHIMPERING]
- INUYASHA.
- HMM?
HI.
THAT WAS SOME NICE WORK YOU DID
AGAINST THIS
LIZARD DEMON, SHIPPO.
- SHIPPO!
- KAGOME.
YOU DEFEATED THE DEMON!
- IT WASN'T ME.
INUYASHA DID IT.
- WELL, THAT LIZARD WAS
ALREADY ON HIS LAST LEGS
BY THE TIME I GOT HERE.
- INUYASHA.
- I THINK THAT THE DEMON MUST
HAVE USED SATSUKI TO GET AT US
HOPING WE COULD BE OVERPOWERED.
- EVERYONE WHO BECOMES INVOLVED
WITH THE SACRED JEWEL
BECOMES UNHAPPY.
I FORGOT THAT,
AND SATSUKI SUFFERED FOR IT.
- HMM?
- I'M SORRY, SATSUKI.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYMORE.
- YOUR STONE!
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE DECIDED TO GO LIVE
WITH THE HEADMAN OF THE VILLAGE.
OH, I'M NOT SAD.
I KNEW ALL ALONG
THAT MY BROTHER WAS GONE.
- TAKE CARE, SATSUKI.
- THANK YOU
FOR EVERYTHING, SHIPPO.
I'M SURE GLAD THAT I MET YOU.
- I'LL HOPE YOU'LL BE HAPPY
ONE DAY, SATSUKI.
I DON'T HAVE A MOTHER
OR FATHER EITHER.
BUT I'M NOT ALONE, SO IT'S OK.
- SHIPPO WAS REALLY QUITE TAKEN
BY THAT YOUNG GIRL.
- I GUESS SO.
- HUH, WHAT'S HE DOING
ACTING LIKE A GROWNUP?
- HE MAY BE LITTLE,
BUT HE'S STILL A MAN.
- THAT WAS HIS FIRST LOVE.
- COME ON, SHIPPO.
WE'RE LEAVING.
- MOVE IT ALONG.
WE HAVEN'T GOT ALL DAY
TO WAIT AROUND.
- I'M COMING.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- THE MEN IN A VILLAGE
ALL DISAPPEAR
AFTER BEING BEWITCHED
BY A DEMON PRINCESS.
MIROKU SETS OUT TO RESCUE THEM,
BUT THE OFFENDER
IS A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN--
HIS ONE WEAKNESS.
THIS COULD BE TROUBLE.
WORRIED, SANGO DECIDES
TO FOLLOW HIM,
AND DEEP IN THE MOUNTAINS
THEY DISCOVER A TRAGIC LEGEND.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.