- THESE OLD LEGS CAN'T KEEP UP.
- I BEAT YOU.
- OH, YOU FOOL.
WE WEREN'T IN A RACE.
LOOK AT THAT, MASTER JAKEN.
IT'S A SLAIN DEMON,
JUST AS LORD SESSHOMARU
EXPLAINED TO US.
- WHO ON EARTH
COULD HAVE DONE THIS?
- INUYASHA.
- LORD SESSHOMARU.
- INUYASHA DID THIS,
ALTHOUGH I DOUBT
HE WAS ABLE TO ESCAPE UNSCATHED.
- AAH!
- I CAN SMELL IT
ON THE DEMON'S FANGS--
THE SCENT OF TETSUSAIGA.
HMM. SO I WAS RIGHT.
THESE FANGS
BROKE THE SWORD IN HALF.
- AAH!
- COME WITH ME.
- WE'RE TAKING
THE HEAD WITH US?
- ENOUGH OF THAT, RIN.
STOP IT.
- YES, MY LORD.
- THE SCENT IN THE WIND
TELLS ME WHAT TRANSPIRED HERE.
ONE THING BAFFLES ME.
THE SCENT OF INUYASHA'S BLOOD
HAS CHANGED.
IT IS NOT THE SMELL
OF A HALF-DEMON.
INUYASHA'S BLOOD
HAS THE SAME SCENT
AS MY BLOOD...
AND OF OUR FATHER'S.
- WHEN TETSUSAIGA
WAS BIT IN TWO,
I WAS CERTAIN
I WAS GONNA DIE.
MY ENTIRE BODY SUDDENLY BURNED
WITH A DESIRE TO LIVE.
NEXT THING I KNEW,
I'D KILLED GOSHINKI.
AND THAT'S WHEN
I FELT SOMETHING STRANGE,
SOMETHING I'D NEVER
FELT BEFORE...
PURE PLEASURE
FROM KILLING GOSHINKI.
- HERE.
GRILLED FISH.
THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
- YEAH? THANK YOU.
- OH, SNAP OUT OF IT,
WOULD YOU?
QUIT MOPING
OVER YOUR BROKEN SWORD.
AAH!
THAT'S MY FISH.
- NOT ANYMORE.
- HUH?
- AAH!
- [MOO]
- THE BULL THAT BELONGS
TO TOTOSAI,
THE SWORDSMITH
THAT FORGED TETSUSAIGA.
- IT CAME ALONE?
- MASTER INUYASHA.
[SUCKING]
- MYOGA, YOU FOUND US.
- IT IS HIM.
YOU WERE HIDING OUT
AT MASTER TOTOSAI'S
ALL THIS TIME?
- HOW RUDE,
MAKING ME SOUND
LIKE A COWARD.
- WELL, YOU DID RUN AWAY.
- YEP. YOU SURE DID.
- AHEM.
NEVER MIND THAT.
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED
TO TETSUSAIGA.
WHAT'S THAT?
- A DEMON CALLED GOSHINKI
BIT IT IN HALF
WHILE I WAS FIGHTING HIM.
- JUST AS I SUSPECTED.
THAT EXPLAINS WHY THE SCENT
OF INUYASHA'S BLOOD
HAS CHANGED.
MY LORD, PLEASE,
YOU MUST TAKE THE PIECES
OF THE SWORD
AND GOT TO MASTER TOTOSAI,
TETSUSAIGA'S SWORDSMITH.
- YOU MEAN TETSUSAIGA
CAN BE PUT BACK TOGETHER AGAIN?
- YES! YES!
NOW HURRY, PLEASE!
THERE'S NO TIME TO LOSE.
MOMO THE BULL
WILL TAKE YOU RIGHT
TO TOTOSAI'S HOME.
- RIGHT.
BYE FOR NOW.
- AND YOU ARE CERTAIN
THAT INUYASHA WENT THROUGH
A TRANSFORMATION?
- MM-HMM.
DOES IT HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE TETSUSAIGA
GETTING BROKEN?
- IT DOES.
AS YOU ARE AWARE,
TETSUSAIGA IS AN HEIRLOOM
THAT WAS LEFT TO INUYASHA
BY HIS FATHER.
THE SWORD PROTECTS HIM
FROM HIS ENEMIES,
BUT IT HAS A SECOND PURPOSE:
KEEPING THE DEMON INSIDE
LOCKED UP.
- [GASPS]
- IT KEEPS THE DEMON
LOCKED INSIDE INUYASHA?
- INUYASHA'S DEATH
IS INEVITABLE
ONCE TETSUSAIGA IS BROKEN.
HIS STRONG DESIRE TO LIVE
AWAKENED THE DEMON BLOOD
THAT FLOWS IN HIS VEINS.
- HMM.
- AND EVEN AFTER
TETSUSAIGA IS REPAIRED,
THAT DEMON PART OF INUYASHA
WILL BE EVEN HARDER TO CONTROL
BECAUSE NOW
HE HAS TASTED THE PLEASURE
OF BRUTALLY SLAYING AN ENEMY.
- DOES THAT MEAN
HIS HEART IS BEING TAKEN OVER
BY THE DEMON IN HIM?
- YOU IDIOT!
- INUYASHA.
[SOBBING]
- ONLY A SIMPLETON
WOULD ALLOW THIS TO HAPPEN.
- HMPH.
- WHAT HAS THIS FOOL
DONE TO YOU,
MY PRECIOUS TETSUSAIGA?
- YEAH, YEAH.
NOW CAN YOU STOP BAWLING
AND START FIXING MY SWORD?
- LISTEN, YOUNGSTER,
IT'S NOT QUITE THAT SIMPLE.
- HUH?
YOU MEAN YOU CAN'T FIX IT?
- I AM A MASTER SWORDSMITH.
I CAN REPAIR IT
OVER THE COURSE OF 3 DAYS,
BUT I'LL REQUIRE
SOMETHING TO BOND IT.
- LIKE WHAT?
- OPEN UP FOR ME,
WOULD YOU, INUYASHA?
- HMM?
HOW'S THIS?
AAH!
- WELL, THIS FANG
WILL HAVE TO DO.
- WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
- QUIT YOUR WHINING.
YOUR TOOTH WILL GROW BACK
IN A MERE HALF A DAY.
- GOOD.
YOU'RE GETTING
TO BE A REAL PAIN
IN THE NECK, OLD MAN.
YOU'VE GOT 3 DAYS
TO BRING ME
MY REPAIRED SWORD.
- WHY DO I HAVE JUST 3 DAYS?
- BECAUSE THAT'S HOW LONG
YOU SAID YOU'D NEED TO FIX IT.
- AHH.
- YEAH.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU,
OLD MAN.
LATER.
- GOOD-BYE.
I PROMISE NOT
TO LET YOU DOWN.
- AHH.
WHO ARE YOU?
- YOU ARE KAIJINBO,
I TAKE IT--
THE SMITH WHO FORGED
TOO MANY DEVIANT SWORDS
AND WAS BANISHED BY
HIS MASTER TOTOSAI.
- TOTOSAI, YOU SAY?
THE SOUND OF HIS NAME
IS STILL ENOUGH
TO MAKE MY BLOOD BOIL.
- HOW ABOUT IT, KAIJINBO?
I WOULD HAVE YOU
FORGE A SWORD FOR ME
WITH THE FANGS
OF THIS DEMON.
- DON'T TAKE ME
FOR A FOOL.
I CANNOT MAKE A SWORD
FROM SOMETHING
THAT IS ALREADY DEAD.
- IS LORD SESSHOMARU
GOING TO USE TENSEIGA,
THE SWORD OF HEALING?
- I CAN SEE THE MESSENGERS
FROM THE NETHERWORLD.
- THE DEMON'S HEAD
HAS COME BACK TO LIFE.
- ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN SOMETHING,
KAIJINBO.
- THIS SWORD TENSEIGA
WAS FORGED BY THE SAME MASTER
WHO BANISHED YOU SOME TIME AGO,
AND THE FANGS OF THE DEMON
I LAID HERE BEFORE YOU
BROKE TETSUSAIGA,
A SWORD THAT WAS
ALSO FORGED BY TOTOSAI.
- INCREDIBLE.
- YES, THESE FANGS
WILL FORM A POWERFUL SWORD.
- TETSUSAIGA SHOULD BE
FIXED BY TOMORROW
IF WE'RE LUCKY.
- THIS COULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED
AT A WORSE TIME.
IT'S GONNA BE A LONG NIGHT.
- DAMN HIM.
I WISH THAT TOTOSAI
WOULD HURRY UP
AND BRING ME THE SWORD.
- MY, HE LOOKS LIKE
AN ORDINARY HUMAN NOW.
- I GUESS YOU DIDN'T KNOW THIS
ABOUT INUYASHA.
I HAVE HEARD
THIS HAPPENED TO HIM,
BUT THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE ACTUALLY SEEN IT MYSELF.
YOU SEE, HALF-DEMONS
SUCH AND INUYASHA
LOSE THEIR DEMON POWERS
ON ONE GIVEN NIGHT
WHEN THEY BECOME MERE MORTALS.
LOOK HERE.
NO FANGS, AS YOU SEE.
VERY INTERESTING,
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- COULD YOU GET YOUR KICKS
SOMEWHERE OTHER THAN IN MY FACE?
- MY APOLOGIES.
IF A HALF-DEMON
IS ATTACKED ON SUCH A NIGHT,
HIS LIFE IS IN DANGER.
SO THE NIGHTS THAT
INUYASHA LOSES HIS POWERS
MUST BE KEPT
STRICTLY SECRET.
- AND HOW IS IT THAT
YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS, MIROKU?
SHIPPO, IT WAS YOU!
- LET GO!
THAT HURTS!
- YOU BLABBERMOUTH.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
THAT YOU'D GO AROUND
TELLING EVERYONE.
- I DIDN'T MEAN
TO DO ANY HARM.
- THAT SHOULD GO WITHOUT SAYING,
SHOULDN'T IT?
- DAMN.
THIS IS GREAT.
EVERY TIME I TURN AROUND,
MORE PEOPLE KNOW
ABOUT MY LITTLE SECRET.
- SO WHAT?
IT ONLY PROVES
YOU HAVE MORE FRIENDS
THAN BEFORE.
- WHEN I TURN MORTAL LIKE THIS,
I'M OVERCOME BY
STRONG HUMAN EMOTIONS.
IT'LL BE GOOD RIDDANCE
TO THOSE FEELINGS
ONCE I BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
- INUYASHA?
- THEN AGAIN,
IF I DO BECOME A TRUE DEMON,
HOW WILL I REACT
TO KAGOME AND THE OTHERS?
- HERE.
YOU KNOW, I WOULDN'T WANDER
TOO FAR AWAY FROM US TONIGHT
IF I WERE YOU.
- HUH.
SPARE ME.
EVERYBODY NEEDS
A LITTLE TIME TO THINK,
AND I'M NO EXCEPTION.
- WHAT'S WITH YOU?
- INUYASHA,
DO YOU STILL INTEND
TO BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON?
YOU REALLY SCARED ME
THE OTHER DAY.
- YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN SCARED
OF THE DEMON.
IF I HADN'T
TRANSFORMED WHEN I DID,
YOU ALL WOULD HAVE
BEEN SLAUGHTERED BY GOSHINKI.
- YOU DON'T GET IT.
I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT HOW YOUR FACE CHANGED
OR HOW WE WERE IN DANGER...
- DID I REALLY LOOK
THAT TERRIFYING?
- IT'S JUST--
WHAT SCARED ME THE MOST
WAS THAT IT FELT
LIKE YOU WERE SUDDENLY
OUT OF MY REACH.
I COULDN'T HELP THINKING
THAT YOU WOULD FORGET ABOUT ME.
THAT'S ALL.
- WHEN I TRANSFORMED
THE OTHER DAY,
MY HEART WAS--
COME ON.
DON'T BE SO STUPID.
I'M STILL THE SAME GUY
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS TO ME.
I WOULDN'T FORGET
ABOUT YOU OR MIROKU
AND THE OTHERS.
- MM-HMM.
DON'T FORGET US.
PLEASE DON'T FORGET US,
INUYASHA.
- KAIJINBO,
3 DAYS HAVE PASSED.
HAVE YOU COMPLETED
FORGING THE SWORD
FROM THE DEMON'S FANGS?
- YES.
IT'S DONE.
A MAGNIFICENT DEMON SWORD.
- THIS MUST BE THE WORK
OF KAIJINBO.
- I'M ALIVE.
BUT HOW CAN THAT BE?
WASN'T I DRAWN IN HALF?
I KNEW IT.
- LET'S GO, JAKEN.
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER QUICKLY.
- MY LORD.
IS IT POSSIBLE
THAT YOU REVIVED ME
WITH YOUR TENSEIGA?
- WHO OTHER IS CAPABLE
OF BRINGING SOMEONE BACK
FROM THE DEAD?
- NO ONE, MY LORD.
- HAS KAIJINBO
COMPLETED MY SWORD?
- YES, LORD SESSHOMARU.
HE HAS FORGED A SWORD
FROM THE FANGS
OF THE SLAIN DEMON.
BUT I MUST ADD THAT HIS EYES
HAVE BECOME MOST FEARFUL,
ALMOST AS IF--
AS IF HE HAS BEEN POSSESSED
BY THE SWORD ITSELF.
- HMM.
INTERESTING.
- INUYASHA?
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD
GET SOME SLEEP.
- MIROKU--
AWW, COME OFF IT.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
I'VE NEVER ONCE GONE TO SLEEP
WHILE I WAS TRANSFORMED
INTO A MORTAL.
- TOO SCARED
TO GO TO SLEEP?
- OH, I'M SCARED.
SO WHAT?
- AS LONG AS
YOU'RE BEING HONEST.
- A LOT OF ENEMIES
ARE AFTER ME.
IF ANY OF THEM ATTACK ME
WHEN I'M HUMAN LIKE THIS,
I DON'T STAND
A CHANCE IN HELL.
- THERE MIGHT JUST BE
A LESSON
FOR YOU TO LEARN
FROM ALL THIS.
HMM?
- MIROKU?
SOMETHING IN THE AIR.
- MM-HMM.
- AN EVIL AURA.
- WHICH ONE IS INUYASHA?
- WHY? WHO WANTS TO KNOW?
- MY NAME IS KAIJINBO.
I'M A SWORDSMITH.
- A SWORDSMITH?
- I FORGED THIS SWORD,
THE TOKIJIN,
AND NOW IT CRIES
FOR A TASTE OF THE BLOOD
OF INUYASHA.
- WHY HAS THIS SMITH
COME AFTER ME?
- SO YOU ARE INUYASHA.
THE SWORD HAS TAUGHT ME SO.
DISAPPOINTING.
I EXPECTED A DEMON,
AND YET I AM FACED
WITH A MERE MORTAL.
- INUYASHA, HAVE YOU EVER
WRONGED THIS SWORDSMITH
THAT YOU KNOW OF?
- NO.
- YOU HEARD THE MAN.
- AS I TOLD YOU,
IT IS THE SWORD
THAT THIRSTS FOR HIS BLOOD.
TOKIJIN WAS FORGED
FROM THE FANGS OF THE DEMON
THAT BROKE YOUR TETSUSAIGA,
THE SWORD THAT WAS CREATED
BY OLD TOTOSAI.
- HUH?
HE USED GOSHINKI'S FANGS?
THE SAME MONSTER
THAT BIT MY SWORD IN HALF?
- IN OTHER WORDS,
THE SWORD IS FILLED
WITH GOSHINKI'S HATRED FOR YOU.
- HUH.
I'VE HEARD EVERYTHING
I NEED TO.
PREPARE YOURSELF, KAIJINBO.
I'LL HACK YOU TO PIECES.
- ESCAPE WHILE YOU CAN,
INUYASHA.
- SANGO AND I
WILL TAKE CARE OF THIS DEMON.
- YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE
RIGHT NOW.
- DO AS THEY SAY, INUYASHA.
- DAMN.
- HIRAIKOTSU!
- PITY ABOUT YOUR POOR AIM.
[GASPS]
- SANGO'S WEAPON.
- [CHUCKLES]
YOU FOOL.
- I'LL ADMIT YOUR SWORD
IS FORMIDABLE...
WHICH IS WHY
I'LL HAVE TO RESORT TO THIS.
FAREWELL!
- HE DID IT.
- AND HERE ALL ALONG
I THOUGHT
THAT MIROKU'S ONLY WEAPON
WAS HIS WIND TUNNEL.
HE DOES HAVE SPIRITUAL POWERS.
- BEHIND YOU, MIROKU!
- TOKIJIN IS INVINCIBLE.
NO SWORD CAN MATCH IT.
MY ENEMY ISN'T KAIJINBO,
IT'S THE SWORD.
- [CACKLING]
PLAYTIME IS OVER.
- HE'S ACTING
AS IF NOTHING HAPPENED,
EVEN THOUGH
HIS HEAD IS SPLIT OPEN.
- YEAH, ALMOST AS IF
HE'S CONTROLLED
BY THE TOKIJIN SWORD.
- COME FOR ME, INUYASHA,
OR ARE YOU COMPLETELY
PARALYZED BY FEAR?
WILL YOU RUN AND HIDE
LIKE A CHILD?
- INUYASHA,
DON'T LET HIM LURE YOU
INTO BATTLE.
- I'M NOT GONNA FALL
FOR ANY TRICKS LIKE THAT.
THE THING IS
THAT I'M THE ONLY ONE
THAT HE'S COME AFTER...
AND I'M NOT GONNA
RUN AWAY AND HIDE.
- INUYASHA!
- WHY DOES HE ALWAYS
HAVE TO BE SO STUBBORN?
- [MOO]
- TOTOSAI.
- HAVE YOU REPAIRED
THE TETSUSAIGA?
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
YOU HAD SOMETHING TO DO
WITH ALL THIS COMMOTION.
- YOU'RE LATE,
OR MAYBE YOU HADN'T NOTICED.
THANK YOU.
- MASTER, DON'T DO IT.
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
- TETSUSAIGA WILL NOT TRANSFORM
WHEN YOU ARE IN YOUR HUMAN FORM
WITHOUT YOUR DEMONIC POWERS.
- IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE WE MET, KAIJINBO.
- I TOOK YOU FOR DEAD,
TOTOSAI.
- YOU'VE BEEN BUSY
CRAFTING ANOTHER WICKED SWORD,
HAVEN'T YOU, KAIJINBO?
- TOTOSAI, I SHALL PROVE TO YOU
WITHOUT A DOUBT
WHICH OF US
IS THE BETTER SWORDSMITH.
- TOTOSAI, TELL ME,
ARE YOU FAMILIAR
WITH THIS KAIJINBO PERSON?
- YES. HE WAS ONCE
MY DISCIPLE.
I BANISHED HIM
A LONG TIME AGO.
HE WAS MOST UNORTHODOX.
HE KILLED 10 INNOCENT CHILDREN
FOR HIS SWORD.
WHAT A WRETCHED BEAST.
HE COVERED THE BLADE
WITH HUMAN BLOOD AND OIL
IN ORDER TO MAKE IT
SEETHE WITH HATRED.
- DRAW YOUR SWORD, INUYASHA.
I SHALL CRUSH
TOTOSAI'S CREATION
BEFORE HIS VERY EYES.
- HUH.
I WON'T WASTE ANY TIME
DOING YOU
AND THAT SWORD OF YOURS IN.
- MASTER TOTOSAI,
I HOPE THAT YOU'VE MADE
THE TETSUSAIGA
EVEN STRONGER
THAN IT WAS BEFORE.
- PERHAPS A LITTLE.
- A LITTLE ISN'T ENOUGH.
- KAIJINBO'S SWORD
IS FORGED FROM THE FANG
OF THE DEMON
THAT BROKE TETSUSAIGA.
- HMM.
- INUYASHA!
- [CACKLES]
THIS WILL PUT AN END TO YOU.
- THAT'S A RELIEF,
TETSUSAIGA.
YOU SEEM EVER MORE POWERFUL
THAN BEFORE.
- IT DIDN'T BREAK.
- NOPE.
DIDN'T EXPECT IT WOULD.
- BUT HE'S TOO WEAK
TO HANDLE IT.
- YOUR BODY WILL GIVE IN
LONG BEFORE YOUR SWORD DOES.
- SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU,
KAIJINBO.
THAT SWORD OF YOURS
MAY BE PRETTY STRONG,
BUT YOU'RE NOT NEARLY
SKILLED ENOUGH TO WIELD IT.
YOU SHOULD HAVE KILLED ME
WHILE YOU HAD THE CHANCE...
BEFORE I BECAME
A DEMON AGAIN.
- HE'S TRANSFORMING BACK.
- THE SUN'S COMING UP.
- I'M GONNA TEST
TETSUSAIGA'S NEW BLADE
AND YOU'RE FIRST.
HEY, TOTOSAI,
WHAT THE HELL HAVE YOU DONE
TO MY TETSUSAIGA,
YOU OLD CODGER?
ANSWER ME, OLD MAN.
WHAT DID YOU DO TO MY SWORD?
- WHAT? ARE YOU HAVING
SOME KIND OF PROBLEM?
- AS IF YOU HADN'T NOTICED.
WHY IS THIS THING SO HEAVY?
- OH, IT MUST
HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THAT FANG
OF YOURS I USED.
PAY NO MIND.
- NO GOOD HAVING A SWORD
YOU CAN'T EVEN HOLD.
I'LL SLICE YOU IN HALF,
INUYASHA.
- YOU MIGHT WANT
TO RAISE YOUR SWORD.
- THAT'S THE WHOLE PROBLEM.
- DAMN THAT OLD MAN.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- TOKIJIN, A SWORD FORGED
WITH GOSHINKI'S HATRED,
POSSESSES
THE SWORDSMITH KAIJINBO.
THE POWERFUL WEAPON
IS WIELDED AGAINST INUYASHA,
AND LATER
ITS TRUE OWNER SHOWS UP.
SESSHOMARU,
INUYASHA'S BROTHER,
TURNS TOKIJIN ON HIM,
AS THOUGH TRYING
TO TEST SOMETHING.
THEN KAGURA,
NARAKU'S INCARNATION,
STEPS ON THE STAGE
TO REALLY HEAT THINGS UP.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!