>> ALONG OUR JOURNEY IN SEARCH
OF NARAKU, WE STUMBLE UPON 3
YOUNG MONKEY SPRITES CLUMSY,
SCATTERBRAINED, AND QUICK TO
JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS, YET TOO
CUTE TO HATE.
THE 3 MONKEY SPRITES ARE IN
SEARCH OF A SACRED OBJECT WHICH
HOUSED THEIR MONKEY GOD.
WE FINALLY FIND IT IN A PICKLING
TUB WHERE IT IS BEING USED
AS A WEIGHT.
THE MONKEY GOD TELLS US
SOMETHING VERY STRANGE
AND TROUBLING.
A HUGE DEMONIC AURA HAD PASSED
OVERHEAD AND THEN SUDDENLY
DISAPPEARED.
>> IT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN ANYONE
BUT NARAKU.
>> OX AND TIGER?
OH, THAT'S NORTHEAST.
>> SO, SHALL WE GO?
>> YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WE'VE GOT THE
DIRECTIONS, SO LET'S MOVE.
>> UHH!
THIS ISN'T THE WAY THINGS WERE
SUPPOSED TO TURN OUT.
WHAT ARE WE SITTING
AROUND HERE FOR?
>> AH-CHOO!
I'M SORRY.
>> WOULD YOU BE QUIET
AND LEAVE HER ALONE?
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE WENT OUT
AND CAUGHT HERSELF A COLD
ON PURPOSE, YOU KNOW.
>> I FIGURED OUT THAT MUCH.
>> [KAGOME COUGHS]
I'M SORRY.
I'M HOLDING EVERYONE BACK.
>> STOP WORRYING.
THIS TRIP IS GOING TO BE
A LONG ONE.
WE CAN USE THIS TIME TO GET
THINGS PREPARED.
>> SHE'S RIGHT.
I'LL USE THE TIME TO PREPARE
ALL MY GADGETS.
>> WHAT SHE'S SAYING IS YOUR
COLD IS ACTUALLY A BLESSING
IN DISGUISE.
>> EXACTLY, SO STOP WORRYING
YOURSELF.
>> DAMN IT!
HURRY UP AND GET WELL.
>> DON'T BE SO HARSH.
I REALIZE WE'RE IN A HURRY,
BUT DON'T BLAME KAGOME
FOR GETTING SICK.
>> YES.
>> I AGREE.
OW!
>> THANKS, YOU GUYS.
>> UH!
DAMN!
WHO SAID I WAS BLAMING YOU?
>> GEE, WHAT A HOTHEAD.
>> KAGOME WILL PROBABLY RECOVER
QUICKER IF INUYASHA
ISN'T AROUND.
>> IT'S TOO BAD KAEDE
ISN'T AROUND TO GIVE KAGOME
HER REMEDIES.
>> YOU HAVE A TERRIBLE FEVER.
>> I'M WORRIED, KAGOME.
WOULDN'T YOU BE BETTER OFF TO GO
BACK TO YOUR OWN HOME?
>> HUH?
GO HOME?
>> THE PHYSICIANS THERE DO SEEM
TO BE MORE KNOWLEDGEABLE.
>> AND THEY SEEM TO HAVE BETTER
MEDICATIONS.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HATE TO LEAVE YOU GUYS, BUT I
THINK I'D BETTER GO BACK.
>> THERE'S NO REASON TO
APOLOGIZE TO US FOR YOUR HEALTH.
NOW CLIMB ON MY BACK, KAGOME,
AND I'LL CARRY YOU TO THE WELL.
>> CAN YOU MANAGE, KAGOME?
>> YEAH, I'M OK.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
>> WHY, WHATEVER DO YOU MEAN?
>> YEAH, SHE'LL BE STAYING HOME
FROM SCHOOL AGAIN.
HUH?
IT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN A SIMPLE COLD,
BUT THIS TIME IT'S FOR REAL.
OH, DEAR.
>> KAGOME IS ABSENT AGAIN TODAY.
THIS TIME IT SEEMS
SHE HAS A COLD.
>> A COLD?
THAT'S ALL?
>> OH.
YOU THINK YOU COULD STOMACH
SOMETHING TO EAT?
>> NO CHANCE.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN I'LL MAKE YOU
SOMETHING WARM TO DRINK,
AND YOU CAN TAKE YOUR MEDICINE
AFTER THAT.
>> OK.
[COUGHS]
>> BUT SHE HASN'T BEEN HOME
FOR QUITE SOME TIME.
TOO BAD SHE'S COME DOWN
WITH A COLD.
>> YES, MAYBE IT WAS COLD
WHERE SHE WAS.
>> WELL, SHE SHOULD REST UNTIL
SHE'S FULLY RECOVERED.
I JUST THOUGHT OF SOMETHING.
>> SO SHE STAYED HOME JUST
BECAUSE OF A COLD.
>> YEAH, UP UNTIL NOW SHE WAS
LAID UP WITH SICKNESSES WE'D
NEVER HEARD OF.
>> I KNOW.
>> HEY, DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
GO VISIT HER?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S
GOING TO BE IN THE HOSPITAL
OR ANYTHING.
SHE'S OBVIOUSLY AT HOME.
>> HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
>> IT IS.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN KAGOME
IN A LONG TIME.
>> ARE YOU THINKING OF GOING
TO HER HOUSE?
>> HI.
I DIDN'T SEE YOU STANDING THERE.
>> OUR TEACHER SAYS SHE'S AWAY
WITH A COLD.
>> YEAH?
TOO BAD.
>> DO YOU WANT TO COME WITH US
AND VISIT HER AFTER SCHOOL?
>> SOUNDS SERIOUS.
>> SOUNDS LIKE A DEFINITE MAYBE.
>> THIS COULD BE HARSH.
>> HMM...
>> LADY KAEDE!
>> WE MUST KEEP OUR HEADS,
RIKICHI.
WE MUST STAY CALM AND FOCUSED.
>> YES, BUT IT'S BEEN SOME TIME
SINCE I'VE SLAYED A DEMON.
>> TRY TO BE STRONG.
INUYASHA AND THE OTHERS
AREN'T HERE, SO WE MUST DEAL
WITH IT OURSELVES.
HERE IT COMES!
>> [DEMON ROARS]
>> ATTACK THE BEAST!
>> LADY KAEDE!
>> WHO INVITED YOU HERE?
>> [DEMON SCREAMS]
>> INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU PEOPLE DOING ALL
THE WAY OUT HERE?
>> ALL SORTS OF DEMONS HAVE BEEN
ACTING UP LATELY.
SOME ARE EVEN TERRORIZING AREAS
WHERE HUMANS LIVE.
>> I THINK IT'S BECAUSE OF
NARAKU'S DISAPPEARANCE.
MOST OF THE DEMONS WERE KEEPING
A PRETTY LOW PROFILE WHILE HE
WAS STILL AROUND.
HUH?
NOW THEY'RE DOING
AS THEY PLEASE!
AAH!
>> [DEMON SCREECHING]
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> WAIT!
INUYASHA!
>> DID HE COME ALL THIS WAY
TO SAVE US?
>> HMM...
SOMEHOW I DOUBT THAT WAS
HIS INTENTION.
>> HUH?
YOU'RE IN THE WAY.
MOVE.
>> YOU VILLAINS!
WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO?
>> I COULD CARE LESS
WHO YOU ARE.
I'VE GOT THINGS TO DO IN THIS
SWAMP, AND YOU'RE IN THE WAY.
>> THIS SWAMP IS MY TERRITORY.
FLEE WHILE YOU CAN, OR I'LL
SWALLOW YOU HEADFIRST.
>> MAYBE THIS WILL HELP CLEAR
YOUR MIND.
AAH!
SO MUCH FOR HIM.
NOW...
HUH?
YES.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
>> WHO DARES TO INTRUDE
ON MY VALLEY?
>> OUR WATERFALL!
>> YEAH, YEAH, I HEARD IT
ALL BEFORE.
>> INTRUDER!
>> INTRUDE THIS, BIRDBRAIN!
>> LADY KAEDE, THE DEMONS ARE NO
LONGER COMING AFTER US.
>> HMM...
I WONDER IF THEY ESCAPED
SOMEWHERE.
>> UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I FIGURED SINCE WE WERE
HERE...
>> YOU CAME TO VISIT ME?
THAT'S REALLY NICE OF YOU.
>> GOT A FEVER?
>> YEAH, OFF AND ON.
>> HOW IS YOUR NOSE AND YOUR
THROAT DOING?
>> IT'S MOSTLY JUST A COUGH.
>> THESE ARE FOR YOU.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
>> I KNOW IT'S JUST A COLD, BUT
YOU CAN'T BE TOO CAREFUL.
>> SHE'S RIGHT, ESPECIALLY
CONSIDERING HOW SICK YOU'VE BEEN
LATELY, KAGOME.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
>> DOES YOUR GUY COME TO VISIT
YOU SOMETIMES WHEN YOU'RE SICK?
>> GUY?
>> YOU KNOW, MR. POSSESSIVE.
>> HE'D NEVER COME TO VISIT ME.
>> WHY WOULDN'T HE?
>> SO, HE'S POSSESSIVE, RUDE,
AND THOUGHTLESS.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON HERE ANYWAY?
WHY DON'T YOU HURRY UP
AND GET BETTER?
>> HE DOESN'T LIVE AROUND HERE.
>> LONG DISTANCE RELATIONSHIP.
>> KAGOME!
THERE'S A BOY FROM YOUR SCHOOL
NAMED HOJO HERE TO SEE YOU.
>> HOJO?
>> WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
>> UH, HI.
>> HI, YOURSELF.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> I HEARD YOU CAUGHT A COLD, SO
I THOUGHT I'D BETTER COME TO SEE
HOW YOU'RE DOING.
I'VE BEEN WONDERING WHAT I COULD
DO FOR YOU.
I GAVE IT A LOT OF THOUGHT, BUT
I COULDN'T COME UP WITH MANY
IDEAS, EXCEPT THIS.
EVERY KIND OF FRUIT I COULD LAY
MY HANDS ON.
ALL THIS VITAMIN C HAS GOT TO BE
GOOD FOR YOUR HEALTH.
>> GEE, THANKS.
>> AND ANOTHER THING.
>> THESE CHARMS ARE SUPPOSED TO
BRING YOU GOOD HEALTH.
THEN I REMEMBERED THAT YOUR
FAMILY RUNS A SHRINE, SO YOU
PROBABLY HAVE YOUR OWN ALREADY.
>> THAT'S OK.
OUR CHARMS DON'T WORK TOO WELL,
SO I'LL USE YOURS.
>> HEY!
>> AND THIS, A DUMBBELL.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
IT MIGHT HELP BUILD UP
YOUR STRENGTH.
>> BOY, YOU'RE SO CONSIDERATE.
>> ONE MORE THING.
>> I DON'T NEED ANYTHING ELSE,
REALLY.
>> WOULD YOUR FRIEND LIKE TO
COME IN FOR A FEW MINUTES?
>> HUH?
>> WHAT ARE YOU ALL GAWKING AT?
AND WHERE'S KAGOME?
>> WE SENT HER BACK HOME.
>> BACK HOME?
>> WE THOUGHT SHE'D GET BETTER
CARE IN HER OWN HOME, SO WE SENT
HER BACK TO HER OWN TIME.
>> SHE WENT HOME?
AFTER ALL THE TROUBLE
I WENT TO?
THAT IS THE LAST TIME THAT I--
>> WHAT?
HOW COME YOU TOOK OFF
WITHOUT ME?
>> SHIPPO, YOU--
>> UHH!
COME ON!
CAN'T YOU TAKE A LITTLE JOKE?
WHOA!
>> SHUT UP!
>> WHOA!
THIS LOOKS DELICIOUS.
GET-WELL PRESENTS?
>> NO, IT'S PROBABLY FOR US TO
TAKE ALONG ON OUR UPCOMING
JOURNEY.
>> SOMETHING TELLS ME
YOU'RE WRONG.
>> I'M SURE I'VE PUT IT AWAY
IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
WHERE IS IT?
>> OH, HEY, GRAMPS.
WHATCHA DOING IN THERE?
>> OH!
FOUND IT AT LAST!
THE SECRET MEDICINE PASSED DOWN
THROUGH GENERATIONS OF THE
HIGURACHI FAMILY.
I FINALLY FOUND IT!
HA HA HA HA!
>> GRAMPS.
>> KAGOME'S COLD WILL BE CURED
IN AN INSTANT.
>> WHY DO I BOTHER?
WHOA!
>> [GRAMPS SHOUTS]
MY MEDICINE!
>> UH-OH.
SORRY, GRAMPS.
>> MY MEDICINE!
>> OH, NO.
GRAMPS IS NEVER GONNA
FORGIVE ME.
>> YO.
>> HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING BACK HERE?
>> HOW IS KAGOME'S COLD DOING?
>> SHE'S BEEN GETTING A LOT OF
REST, BUT SOME OF HER FRIENDS
ARE OVER VISITING RIGHT NOW.
>> THAT SO?
>> ALL THE BOYS AT SCHOOL ARE
GOING NUTS ABOUT IT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT AYUMI DID?
>> WOULD YOU STOP IT ALREADY?
>> EVERYONE IN MY CLASS WAS
TALKING ABOUT IT AS WELL.
>> OH, NO!
>> I'LL BET IT'S ALL OVER
THE SCHOOL.
HA HA!
>> I KNOW IT IS.
>> I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> AAH!
>> DIDN'T TAKE MUCH
TO GET YOU HERE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> THE FACT THAT YOU'RE
AT KAGOME'S.
>> I JUST CAME TO SEE
HOW SHE WAS.
>> YOU'RE NICER THAN MOST GUYS.
>> YOU REALLY THINK SO?
>> HE DOESN'T KNOW AFTER ALL.
>> HE HAS NO IDEA THAT KAGOME
HAS A BOYFRIEND.
>> I HEARD THAT KAGOME'S
BOYFRIEND IS ONE OF THE NICEST
GUYS YOU'LL EVER MEET.
>> BOYFRIEND?
I GUESS YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT ME.
>> UH...
>> ACTUALLY,
I MEANT THAT KAGOME--
>> DON'T LISTEN TO HER.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT SHE'S SAYING.
IT'S JUST THERE'S BEEN A GUY WHO
HAS BEEN BOTHERING KAGOME.
>> A FRIEND KIND OF GUY
WHO DOESN'T COME TO SEE HER
WHEN SHE'S SICK.
>> SCHOOL SEEMS LIKE SO MUCH
FUN.
HUH?
>> HI.
WHATCHA DOING?
>> NOT MUCH.
WHAT'S UP?
>> INUYASHA'S HERE.
>> HUH?
>> [CAT GROWLING]
>> INUYASHA.
>> YO.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> NOTHING.
JUST CAME TO CHECK IN, REALLY.
>> YOU WERE WORRIED ABOUT ME,
THEN?
>> NO, I CAME FOR SHIPPO
AND SANGO.
THEY WERE WORRIED.
BUT I'M THE ONLY ONE ABLE TO
COME THROUGH THE WELL, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
I FEEL A LITTLE BIT BETTER
ALREADY, BUT MY FEVER HASN'T
DROPPED YET, AND I STILL COULD
USE SOME MORE REST.
>> HMM.
LET'S GET ONE THING STRAIGHT,
MISSY.
I DIDN'T COME HERE TO TAKE YOU
BACK, YOU KNOW.
YOUR HEALTH IS IMPORTANT.
IF YOU GET WELL FASTER BACK
HERE, WELL, THEN I SUP--
HUH?
SHE'S GONE.
>> [COUGHS]
HUH?
>> HELLO, KAGOME.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> NOTHING.
WELL...
I WAS WONDERING IF ANYTHING WAS
TROUBLING YOU.
>> WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
I DON'T THINK SO.
>> LISTEN, KAGOME, I REALLY
DON'T MIND, YOU KNOW.
IT'S JUST THAT I WISH--
I WISH YOU WOULD COME TO ME WHEN
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
IF SOMETHING IS BUGGING YOU,
THEN I'LL DO WHAT I CAN
TO HELP YOU.
I WANT YOU TO OPEN UP TO ME.
I MEAN, WE'RE BASICALLY GOING
OUT, RIGHT, SO...
UH, HELLO?
>> HEY, GUYS, I THINK WE BETTER
GET GOING.
>> I GUESS SO.
>> HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> TOMORROW'S A BIG
COMPREHENSION TEST, REMEMBER?
>> A TEST!
>> AND IT'S GOING TO BE USED TO
DETERMINE WHAT COURSES WE TAKE
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
>> IT'S WHAT?
>> HAVE YOU BEEN STUDYING WHILE
YOU'VE BEEN AWAY FROM SCHOOL?
>> NOT AS MUCH AS I SHOULD HAVE.
>> IT'S OK.
KAGOME CAN'T HELP IT.
BESIDES, SHE'S NOT EVEN SURE IF
SHE CAN MAKE IT TO SCHOOL
TOMORROW.
>> SO, WHAT'S EXACTLY GONNA BE
ON THE TEST TOMORROW?
>> WHAT?
YOU PLAN ON TAKING THE TEST WHEN
YOU'RE SICK?
>> SURE I DO.
>> KAGOME, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> HOJO, I NEED YOU TO HELP ME.
>> HUH.
I KNEW IT.
THERE IS SOMETHING
TROUBLING YOU.
>> I NEED YOU TO HELP ME STUDY.
>> SHE SHOULD BE IN BED RESTING
NOT PORING OVER BOOKS.
>> THE TEACHERS SAY THERE'S
GOING TO BE A STRONG EMPHASIS ON
MATH AND SCIENCE.
BETTER MEMORIZE YOUR FORMULAS
AND--
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, KAGOME?
YOU SHOULD BE IN BED RESTING.
>> I AM FINE.
LET'S GET BACK TO THE TEST.
>> SEE YOU, KAGOME.
>> YEAH, THANKS FOR COMING
TO VISIT.
>> GET BETTER.
SEE YOU SOON.
>> YEAH, THANKS FOR HELPING ME
STUDY FOR THE TEST.
WHAT IS IT?
>> NOTHING AT ALL.
SEE YA!
>> REST UP.
>> BYE!
>> GO, GIRLS!
>> HEY.
>> YEAH?
>> IS THIS TEST THING OF YOURS
REALLY WORTH IT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> SHOULDN'T YOU BE
CONCENTRATING ON GETTING BETTER
RATHER THAN GOING OUT
FOR THIS TEST?
>> AS SOON AS I'M BETTER, I'LL
HAVE TO GO TO SCHOOL, SO I HAVE
TO STUDY.
>> GETTING BETTER
IS MORE IMPORTANT.
>> THEY'RE BOTH IMPORTANT.
>> PUT THE BOOKS AWAY
AND GET INTO BED.
>> NO!
>> KAGOME!
>> I WANT TO GO TO SCHOOL,
YOU KNOW.
>> HUH?
>> GO AWAY AND QUIT INTERFERING
WITH MY STUDIES!
>> WHAT?
FINE.
HAVE IT YOUR WAY.
>> I'M SO STUPID.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
>> KAGOME, HOW ARE YOU FEELING,
DEAR?
DO YOU THINK YOU MIGHT BE ABLE
TO STOMACH A BOWL
OF RICE PORRIDGE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHOA!
>> IT'S ALL SO GOOD, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO EAT FIRST.
>> YOU KNOW, WE COULD PROBABLY
SELL IT AND MAKE GOOD MONEY.
>> I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD
TOUCH IT.
IT'S NOT EVEN OURS.
KILALA...
>> UH, I HAVEN'T TOUCHED A
THING, HONEST, I HAVEN'T.
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
>> NEITHER HAVE I.
>> INUYASHA?
>> [SIGHS]
MY HEAD IS GONNA SPLIT IN TWO.
>> YO.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU WENT BACK ALREADY.
>> DO YOU GUYS HAVE A COOKING
POT I COULD USE?
>> A POT?
>> WILL A METAL ONE DO?
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> THERE'S NOTHING LIKE LIVER
WHEN IT COMES TO NOURISHMENT.
BOAR LIVER, CARP LIVER, CHICKEN
LIVER, AND SOME MEDICINAL ROOTS
AND HERBS.
>> ARE YOU REALLY GONNA EAT
ALL THAT?
>> NOPE, NOT ME.
>> NOT YOU, THEN--
>> LET'S COOK.
>> HUH?
INUYASHA.
>> HERE.
IT'S MEDICINE.
DRINK UP.
>> MEDICINE?
>> EW, IT STINKS.
>> I PROMISE YOU'LL GET BETTER
IF YOU DRINK.
IT'LL CURE ANY COLD
IN AN INSTANT.
>> IT'S PUTRID!
>> SO WHAT?
IT MIGHT TASTE BAD, BUT IT'LL
DEFINITELY WORK.
>> WOW, DID YOU MAKE THIS
YOURSELF?
>> SURE DID.
>> WELL, IF YOU'RE SURE
IT'LL WORK, I GUESS I CAN CHOKE
IT DOWN.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> JUST TRUST ME.
>> OK.
>> UGH...
SHE'S DRINKING IT.
SIS IS ACTUALLY DRINKING
LIVER POTION.
LIVER...
UGH...
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I THINK IT'S WORKING.
>> TOLD YOU.
>> THANKS A LOT.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET
ALL MUSHY.
>> SO TELL ME, HOW DID YOU KNOW
ABOUT MAKING SUCH A GREAT COLD
MEDICINE?
>> MY, UH,
MOTHER USED TO MAKE IT.
>> YOUR MOTHER?
AND SHE TAUGHT YOU
HOW TO MAKE IT?
>> WELL, THE INGREDIENTS
ARE A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
WHEN SHE MADE IT, SHE USED TO
USE DRIED INGREDIENTS.
BUT I USED FRESH STUFF.
>> FRESH STUFF?
FRESH WHAT EXACTLY?
>> WELL, FRESH--
UH, WHO CARES?
AS LONG AS IT WORKS.
>> I GUESS.
THANKS AGAIN.
>> WOULD YOU STOP THANKING ME?
>> SORRY I YELLED AT YOU.
>> FORGET ABOUT IT, OK?
JUST GO TO SLEEP.
>> OK.
IS THAT SOME KIND OF
MAGIC SPELL?
>> YEAH.
MY MOTHER USED TO DO IT A LONG
TIME AGO.
>> OH.
>> I'M OFF!
>> HEY.
>> MORNING.
>> FEELING ANY BETTER
THIS MORNING?
>> MM-HMM.
I HAVEN'T FELT THIS GOOD
IN AGES.
THAT MEDICINE OF YOURS
REALLY WORKED.
>> SEE, I TOLD YOU IT WOULD.
>> I CAN GO TO SCHOOL
FOR A CHANGE.
I BET I'LL EVEN PASS THE
COMPREHENSION TEST.
AAH!
I'LL NEVER MAKE IT TO SCHOOL
ON TIME!
EVEN IF I LEFT NOW I'D BE LATE!
WHICH MEANS I WON'T BE ON TIME
FOR THE TEST.
>> WELL, WHAT ABOUT
IF YOU HURRY?
>> I'D NEVER GET THERE IN TIME.
>> HURRY UP AND GET CHANGED.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, INUYASHA?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DO YOU THINK YOU'LL MAKE IT?
>> YEAH.
YAY! MORNING.
>> KAGOME, YOU'RE HERE.
>> SO, HOW'S YOUR COLD?
>> WELL, I HAD A GREAT NIGHT'S
SLEEP, AND I FEEL WAY BETTER
TODAY.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE TEST?
>> I'M GONNA GIVE IT MY BEST.
>> ATTA GIRL.
>> TAKE YOUR SEATS, PLEASE.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> SAY, INUYASHA, I HAVE TO TALK
TO YOU MAN-TO-MAN.
>> ABOUT?
>> WHAT'S LOVE?
>> UH...
>> I MEAN, WHAT'S ETERNAL LOVE?
>> WHERE'S ALL THIS COMING FROM?
>> I LOVE HITOMI!
>> KAGOME, DO SOMETHING!
>> LEAVE IT TO ME.
I'LL DO ANYTHING FOR MY DARLING
LITTLE BROTHER.
NEXT, ON "INUYASHA..."
>> OH, THIS IS WAY HARDER THAN
SLAYING DEMONS.