- EVEN IF I AM PROVIDED
WITH ANOTHER ARM,
IT SHALL ALSO BE USELESS
AFTER A SHORT PERIOD.
- A VEXING PROBLEM, ISN'T IT?
[SCREAMS]
- PERHAPS I CAN BE
OF ASSISTANCE.
MIGHT I SUGGEST THAT
YOU EMPLOY THIS ARM?
THIS ARM BELONGED TO A MORTAL,
BUT EMBEDDED IN IT IS A SHARD
OF THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL.
[SHRIEKING]
- WITH ONE STROKE,
I SHALL SLAUGHTER 100 DEMONS.
- SESSHOMARU, I'VE GOT YOU NOW!
I'LL SHOOT YOUR LEFT ARM OFF!
- HUH?
WHY HIS ARM?
- THERE IT IS.
SAY GOOD-BYE TO YOUR SHARD!
- HUH?
NO, YOU DON'T!
UNH!
- AAH!
- LEAVE HER OUT OF THIS!
I'M THE ONE YOU REALLY WANT!
MMF.
[GASP]
- MOST AMUSING.
YOU SEEM SO ANXIOUS
FOR HER SAFETY.
- LET ME AT HIM!
THERE'S A SHARD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
EMBEDDED IN HIS LEFT ARM.
I'M SURE I CAN HIT IT.
- FORGET IT, KAGOME.
- HUH?
- SESSHOMARU HAS NEVER BEEN
THE KIND OF OPPONENT
THAT'S EASY TO STRIKE DOWN.
STAY HERE AND CARE FOR MIROKU.
THE REMEDIES FROM YOUR ERA
SEEM POWERFUL.
MAYBE YOU'LL BE
ABLE TO SAVE HIM.
- I'M ON IT.
- KAGOME?
- YEAH?
- THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
WITH YOUR ARROW,
YOU REVERSED
THE TETSUSAIGA'S TRANSFORMATION.
NOW I CAN DEFEAT HIM.
[THINKING]
- HE'S THANKING ME?
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
IS IT A SIGN OF WEAKNESS?
- THE TRANSFORMATION WAS STOPPED
BY AN ARROW...
OF A MORTAL GIRL, NO LESS.
I SUPPOSE THE TETSUSAIGA
DIDN'T TAKE TO ME.
- LORD SESSHOMARU
APPEARS TO BE WOUNDED.
- UNH!
GRRR...
- METHINKS YOUR
EARLIER EXPRESSION
WAS MORE PLEASING TO THE EYE
AND LESS MENACING TO THE HEAD.
AAH!
- WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING, YOU LITTLE IMP?
- GOING TO A...FUNERAL?
- UH-OH.
SOMETHING TELLS ME THINGS ARE
GONNA GET VIOLENT.
- NOW, CONFESS,
YOU NASTY LITTLE BEAST!
WHERE DID YOU GET
THOSE POISONOUS INSECTS?
- THEY WERE GIVEN TO US
BY A DEMON.
I DID NOT SEE HIS FACE,
FOR HE WORE A MASK OF A BABOON
TO CONCEAL HIMSELF.
- HUH?
AND WHAT WAS HIS NAME?
- NAME?
- MY APOLOGIES.
CALL ME NARAKU.
- NARAKU.
- DID YOU SAY NARAKU?
IT MUST BE THE SAME DEMON
YOU'RE PURSUING.
- TELL ME HIS WHEREABOUTS.
WHERE CAN I FIND HIM?
- I KNOW NOT WHERE HE IS.
AND EVEN IF YOU WERE
TO FIND HIM,
IT WOULD DO YOU NO GOOD.
YOUR FATE HAS BEEN SEALED.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR YOU,
FOR THE POISON HAS TAKEN HOLD
AND SOON WILL CLAIM YOUR LIFE.
- UH...ARE YOU IN PAIN, MIROKU?
- PAIN'S NOTHING.
IT IS DEATH THAT CONCERNS ME...
AND MY WRETCHED FATE
AS A MERE MORTAL.
- DON'T LOOK TO ME FOR SYMPATHY.
[GRUNTING]
- OOH...OHH..
[PUNCHING]
I REALLY SHOULD
KEEP MY MOUTH SHUT.
- UH...
- MIROKU!
- I'M FINE.
I JUST NEED TO REST.
THE IMP MUST BE RIGHT
ABOUT THE POISON.
IT'S GETTING MORE DIFFICULT
TO BREATHE.
- SHIPPO!
- HUH?
- HOW'S HE DOING?
- NOT WELL.
HE'S GOTTEN WORSE.
- HANG ON.
[THINKING]
I'VE GOT TO GET SOME ANTIDOTE
INTO HIM FAST.
I NEED YOU
TO TAKE THIS MEDICINE.
THINK YOU CAN SIT UP?
- UH...NO.
I'M TOO WEAK.
PASS IT THROUGH YOUR MOUTH.
- GOOD IDEA.
- UH?
[CAN OPENS]
- HUH?
MMMFFF...
- I THINK I CAN MANAGE
ON MY OWN.
[THINKING]
- MIROKU HAS ENOUGH ENERGY
TO JOKE AROUND,
SO I KNOW HE'S OK
FOR THE TIME BEING,
BUT HE MIGHT BE
IN SERIOUS DANGER
IF INUYASHA'S BATTLE
DRAGS ON MUCH LONGER.
- I'VE FIGURED YOU OUT,
SESSHOMARU.
BECAUSE YOU'RE A DEMON,
YOU SHOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO GRASP THE TETSUSAIGA.
THAT LEFT ARM OF YOURS
MUST BELONG TO A HUMAN.
YOU'RE USING A SHARD
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
TO CONNECT THE ARM TO YOUR BODY.
IF I CAN LOP OFF THAT HUMAN ARM,
YOU'LL NO LONGER HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES
TO HOLD ON TO THE TETSUSAIGA.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
WHEN YOU LOSE THAT ARM,
I'LL HAVE MYSELF YET ANOTHER
SHARD OF THE JEWEL!
- LET'S SEE YOU TRY TO
TAKE THIS ARM AWAY FROM ME.
[GRUNTING]
- IRON REAPER!
- YOU DID IT!
YOU BROKE THROUGH HIS ARMOR!
HA HA!
- I WAS TRYING TO HIT
THE JEWEL IN HIS ARM.
- UHH.
KAGOME!
- INUYASHA, MAKE HER STOP.
HALF-DEMON THOUGH YOU ARE,
THE BLOOD OF A DEMON
RUNS IN YOU.
BE PROUD OF THAT.
DO NOT ACCEPT HUMAN AID,
EVEN IN DEATH.
- DON'T TRY ANYTHING, KAGOME.
SESSHOMARU IS TOTALLY RUTHLESS.
- I CAN HANDLE IT.
I'LL HIT HIM.
WHAT?
IT MELTED IN HIS HAND!
- YOU'VE HAD YOUR WARNING.
NOW I SHALL PUT AN END
TO YOUR INTERFERENCE!
- OH, NO.
- LOOK OUT, KAGOME!
- AAH!
- UHH! UHH!
[SCREAMING]
UHH!
YOU'RE NOT HURT, ARE YOU?
[GROANS]
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
KAGOME!
[GROANS]
YOU'LL REGRET THAT, SESSHOMARU!
SHE DOESN'T DESERVE IT!
MIROKU!
- THE TETSUSAIGA IS NOT
FULLY TRANSFORMED,
BUT IT HAS SUCH POWER.
THERE IS ONLY ONE METHOD LEFT
TO COUNTER HIM AND THE SWORD.
I MUST ATTACK
WITH MY WIND TUNNEL.
- BETTER RETHINK THAT.
REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
LAST TIME YOU OPENED IT.
[BUZZING]
- THEY'RE...STILL HERE.
- DON'T DO IT, MIROKU.
YOU'RE DOOMED IF YOU
TAKE IN ANY MORE VENOM.
- TAKE KAGOME AND GET
OUT OF HERE, FAST.
GET AS FAR AWAY AS YOU CAN.
- UH, YOU SURE?
- GET KAGOME OUT OF HERE.
GUARD HER WITH YOUR LIFE.
- HMM.
- YOU WILL NEVER ESCAPE ME.
I SHALL DESTROY YOU ALL
WITH A SINGLE STROKE.
AARRRGGGHH!
[GRUNTING]
- THE BLAST HAS SUBSIDED.
INUYASHA'S STAVING OFF
THE SWORD.
- HEY!
WHY ARE YOU WAITING?
RUN FOR IT!
- WE'RE GOING.
[GRUNTING]
- VERY TOUCHING.
TRYING TO BUY TIME IN ORDER
TO SAVE THE LIVES
OF YOUR FRIENDS.
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- HUH?
UH.
- INUYASHA!
- STOP!
- LET GO OF ME!
- HE WANTS TO DEAL WITH THIS
ON HIS OWN.
THAT'S WHY HE TOLD US
TO RUN TO SAFETY.
[GASP]
- INUYASHA.
[GROANING]
- ANY LAST WORDS
BEFORE YOUR TRAGIC DEMISE?
- YOUR IGNORANCE SURPRISES ME.
I REALLY THOUGHT YOU WOULD HAVE
REALIZED IT BY NOW.
- NOTICED WHAT?
- THAT THE SWORD
IS BACK IN MY HANDS!
- MASTER!
WITHOUT THE HUMAN ARM,
YOU'RE UNABLE TO HOLD ON
TO THE TETSUSAIGA.
[GRUNTING]
- HE'S WEAKENING.
- LOOK, SESSHOMARU!
IT SEEMS INUYASHA HAS FINALLY
LOST CONSCIOUSNESS.
- DO NOT APPROACH ANY CLOSER.
- HUH?
HUH?
AAH!
WHOA, WHOA!
[SCREAMING]
[MUMBLING]
WH-WHAT HAPPENED?
THE SWORD ATTACKED
OF ITS OWN ACCORD!
- HE HOLDS POWER OVER IT,
DESPITE BEING UNCONSCIOUS.
[THINKING]
IF I MAKE A MOVE FOR HIM,
HE WILL STRIKE ME DOWN.
WE SHALL LEAVE, JAKEN.
THE TETSUSAIGA IS PRESENTLY
BEYOND MY REACH,
SO THERE'S NO SENSE IN STAYING.
- I WON'T ARGUE
WITH YOUR DECISION.
AFTER YOU, MASTER.
- THEY MUST HAVE GIVEN UP.
- THAT'S A LUCKY BREAK.
[GASP]
- INUYASHA!
[PANTING]
- KAGOME.
[THINKING]
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
[GROANING]
- INUYASHA!
[BUZZING]
- HOW FAR WILL THESE
CURSED INSECTS FOLLOW US?!
- BE PATIENT.
ULTIMATELY, IT IS THE JEWEL
THEY'RE AFTER.
SURELY THEY'RE WAITING FOR ME
TO DISCARD THE ARM.
- THE ARM IS BURNING
AT THE JOINT, MASTER.
THE FIRE LICKS AT YOUR SHOULDER.
- THIS WRETCHED ARM
THREATENS TO BURN ME ALIVE.
- THE PITIFUL SOUL.
I SEE HE FAILED.
HUH?
LORD SESSHOMARU,
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
- NARAKU!
YOU GAVE THAT MISERABLE
HUMAN ARM TO MASTER SESSHOMARU
IN THE HOPES THAT
IT WOULD DESTROY HIM!
- YOU ARE MISTAKEN.
I MERELY WISHED TO ASSIST HIM...
AND, OF COURSE, TO HAVE
MY JEWEL SHARD RETURNED TO ME.
- I SUPPOSE THAT MAKES SENSE.
[GASP]
- SERVES YOU RIGHT FOR PUTTING
MY MASTER IN SUCH JEOPARDY.
- SO, HE ESCAPED.
- HUH?
OH.
HMM.
WH-WHERE DID HE GO?
- LORD SESSHOMARU.
- HUH?
HMM.
I IMPLORE YOU
TO CONTAIN YOUR ANGER.
I MAY CALL ON YOU AGAIN,
SHOULD ANOTHER OPPORTUNITY ARISE
TO DESTROY INUYASHA.
- A CRAFTY
AND AUDACIOUS CHARACTER.
- HACHI, WE'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR A LONG TIME.
- TAKE CHEER, MY FRIEND.
NO NEED FOR
DEATHBED SENTIMENTALITY.
- FEELING ANY BETTER
AFTER TAKING THE ANTIDOTE?
- I BELIEVE YOUR REMEDY HAS
INDEED STARTED TO TAKE EFFECT.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE, KAGOME.
HACHI, I COULD USE
SOMETHING TO EAT.
- GLAD TO HEAR YOU'VE
REGAINED YOUR APPETITE.
[GROANING]
- HOW IS HE?
NOTICE ANY CHANGES?
- HE'S HARDLY MOVED
THE ENTIRE TIME.
[THINKING]
- INUYASHA SAID HE WANTED
TO BE TAKEN HOME.
FOR HIM TO SAY THAT,
HIS INJURIES MUST BE SERIOUS.
SHIPPO, TELL ME MORE
ABOUT THAT HIVE.
- ACCORDING TO THE IMP,
IT WAS NARAKU WHO
LENT THE HIVE TO SESSHOMARU.
NARAKU WAS THE ONE WHO
BURNED THE WIND TUNNEL
IN MIROKU'S HAND, REMEMBER?
[THINKING]
- YEAH.
AND THE DEMON THAT SET
KIKYO AND INUYASHA
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
NOW INUYASHA
WANTS TO DESTROY NARAKU
TO AVENGE KIKYO'S DEATH.
DOES INUYASHA KNOW
ABOUT ALL THIS?
- NO.
HE NEEDED ALL HIS ENERGY
TO BATTLE SESSHOMARU,
AND I KNEW
THIS NEWS ABOUT NARAKU
WOULD INFURIATE HIM,
AND THE LAST THING HE NEEDED
WAS A DISTRACTION.
- LET'S NOT TELL HIM
RIGHT AWAY.
OK, SHIPPO?
OTHERWISE,
HE'LL GO AFTER NARAKU,
AND HE'S JUST TOO
WEAK AND INJURED TO DO IT.
WE'LL TELL HIM EVENTUALLY,
BUT RIGHT NOW,
LET'S CONCENTRATE ON
HELPING HIM RECOVER.
- GOOD IDEA.
[GROANS]
- NARAKU.
HE'S CLOSE AT HAND.
NARAKU, THE CURSED DEMON
WHO DISGUISED HIMSELF AS ME
TO GET CLOSE ENOUGH
TO END KIKYO'S LIFE.
AND NOW HE'S RETURNED
AND IS HIDING NEARBY.
- UHH!
[GROANING]
HUH?
- FOOL.
I HAVE NO DESIRE WHATSOEVER
TO BECOME HUMAN.
- UH?
- IT WASN'T ME.
- BUT I SHALL TAKE
THE SHIKON JEWEL NONETHELESS.
THANKS.
- IT WASN'T ME!
I DIDN'T BETRAY YOU, KIKYO!
- YOU...TRAITOR.
TRAITOR!
- HE SHOWS UP WHEN THERE'S
A SHARD OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
TO BE FOUND.
HE'S NEAR.
- THANKS FOR THE RIDE, HACHI.
WE REALLY OWE YOU ONE.
- DON'T MENTION IT.
- A TOKEN OF APPRECIATION.
- HMM!
IT'S CURRENCY
AND NOT A ROLL OF LEAVES,
I HOPE.
- HMM.
- KAGOME.
- HMM?
- COME WITH ME.
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE UP.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU'RE
STRONGER THAN HUMANS,
BUT THAT'S A SERIOUS INJURY.
IT'S STILL TOO EARLY FOR YOU
TO BE MOVING AROUND.
[GRUNTS]
SEE?
WHAT'D I TELL YOU?
[GROANING]
- WHO INVITED YOU?!
QUIT FOLLOWING!
HUH!
- HUH?
[THINKING]
- MAYBE HE'S NOT IN
SUCH BAD SHAPE AFTER ALL.
HUH?
- HMM?
- AH!
THIS IS THE HERB
THAT KAEDE TOLD ME
WAS THE BEST ANTIDOTE
FOR ALL KINDS OF POISON.
I'LL BREW SOME UP FOR YOU LATER.
AND THIS HERB MAKES
A GOOD ANTISEPTIC.
IT REALLY WORKS,
BUT, BOY, DOES IT STING!
- YOU'VE LEARNED A LOT.
- I GUESS.
- KAGOME, YOU'VE GROWN STRONGER.
- WELL, YOU FINALLY NOTICED.
HOW COULD I NOT GET STRONGER,
RUNNING FROM DEMONS
DAY AFTER DAY?
I'VE LEARNED A LOT MORE
THAN YOUR AVERAGE TEENAGER,
IF I DO SAY SO MYSELF.
AND MY ARCHERY'S
NOT TOO SHABBY, EITHER.
THE BONE EATER'S WELL.
THIS WELL CONNECTS THE PRESENT
WITH THESE TIMES,
THE WARRING STATES ERA.
AND INSIDE MY BODY
WAS THE SACRED JEWEL
WHICH SO MANY DEMONS SEEK.
THAT'S HOW I CAME TO ARRIVE
IN THIS ERA
AND MET INUYASHA.
[GRUNTING]
- KAGOME, I HAVEN'T ASKED
HOW YOU'RE FEELING.
YOU'RE HURT, TOO.
- HUH?
IT'S JUST A LITTLE
LUMP ON THE HEAD.
I'M SORRY, INUYASHA.
YOU TOLD ME TO STAY AWAY
FROM SESSHOMARU,
BUT I DIDN'T LISTEN
AND ONLY MADE THINGS WORSE.
IF I HAD RUN AWAY
LIKE YOU TOLD ME,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
SO SERIOUSLY INJURED.
- NO.
IN THE END,
IT WAS YOU WHO SAVED ME
WITH YOUR ARROW.
I'M GRATEFUL, KAGOME.
[THINKING]
- HE'S GRATEFUL?
OK, NOW HE'S OFFICIALLY
FREAKING ME OUT.
YOU'RE ACTING TOTALLY WEIRD NOW.
DO YOU HAVE A FEVER?
- WHAT'S INUYASHA DOING,
TAKING KAGOME SO DEEP
INTO THE FOREST?
- SHH.
YOU HEARD THE STORY,
ABOUT HOW NARAKU
DECEIVED ME 50 YEARS AGO.
HE'S THE ONE PULLING THE STRINGS
BEHIND SESSHOMARU.
[THINKING]
- HE FIGURED IT OUT.
I GUESS IT'S NO SURPRISE.
INUYASHA'S MORE AWARE
OF NARAKU'S MOVEMENTS
THAN ANYONE.
- I'VE MADE A DECISION.
- HUH?
- THINGS ARE GETTING
MORE DANGEROUS BY THE DAY.
- YEAH, YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
- HUH?
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
AREN'T YOU SCARED?
WE'RE IN SERIOUS DANGER!
THIS TIME, WE WERE LUCKY,
BUT WHO KNOWS ABOUT NEXT TIME?
- WELL, I'M NOT AFRAID!
NARAKU'S A TERRIBLE DEMON.
WE'VE GOT TO DO WHAT WE CAN
TO DESTROY HIM.
HUH?
[THINKING]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
INUYASHA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I WAS AFRAID.
- HUH?
- I THOUGHT I WAS
GOING TO LOSE YOU.
I WAS TERRIFIED.
- LET ME GO!
I WANT TO SEE!
WHAT'S HE DOING?
- THIS ISN'T SOMETHING
FOR CHILDREN TO SEE.
[GRUNTING]
- UH--HUH?
- I'LL HANG ON TO THE JEWEL.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
HUH?
- KAGOME, GO BACK
TO YOUR OWN ERA!
- HMM?
UH...AH...
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA, WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?!
- KAGOME IS GONE.
- WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?!
- I'VE SENT HER BACK HOME,
TO HER OWN TIME
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE WELL.
- UH...
[GRUNTS]
- WHY'D HE PUSH ME LIKE THAT?
HE'S MORE THAN JUST HALF-DEMON.
I'LL GO BACK
AND TEACH HIM A LESSON!
OOP!
[GASPING]
HUH?
THAT'S THE SCHOOL ALARM.
THAT MEANS...
I'M BACK IN MY OWN TIME.
I CAN'T GET BACK
TO THE WARRING STATES ERA.
BUT WHY NOT?
[GASP]
I DON'T HAVE
MY JEWEL SHARDS ANYMORE!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- I WAS HELD BY A BOY
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME.
IF I FIND OUT INUYASHA HUGGED ME
JUST SO HE COULD RIP OFF
THE SHIKON JEWEL SHARDS,
HE'LL BE SORRY.
WHILE INUYASHA TRIES TO RECOVER
FROM HIS INJURIES,
YET ANOTHER DEMON ATTACKS HIM.
IT HAS TO BE
MORE THAN A COINCIDENCE.
SOMEONE WICKED IS NEARBY,
WATCHING AND WAITING.
KAEDE, DO YOU KNOW WHAT
NARAKU REALLY LOOKS LIKE?
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.