- SURE IS
QUIET AND PEACEFUL OUT.
- YOU SAID IT.
OUR BATTLES SEEM JUST LIKE
A BAD DREAM.
[GASP]
I CAN SENSE
A SHIKON JEWEL SHARD.
- WHAT?
- AND IT'S CLOSING IN, FAST!
[ALL SCREAM]
- YO.
- IT'S KOGA.
- I PICKED UP ON
YOUR SCENT, KAGOME,
SO I CAME TO SEE YA.
YOU'VE BEEN WELL, I HOPE?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT,
YOU MANGY WOLF?
[GROWLS]
- COME ON, DON'T GO
PICKING A FIGHT ALREADY.
- STAY OUT OF IT.
I MAY HAVE TO KILL HIM,
OR WORSE.
- PSHAW.
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED
ONE BIT, MUTT.
YOU'D THINK YOU COULD LOSE
THE ARROGANCE ONCE IN A WHILE.
KAGOME, DON'T YOU GET TIRED
OF BEING WITH THIS GUY?
- UH-OH.
- YOU--
- DON'T BE SO RUDE
TO MY POOR FRIEND, KOGA.
YOU SEE, HE'S NOT
ALWAYS LIKE THIS.
HE JUST GETS UPTIGHT
WHEN YOU COME AROUND,
BECAUSE HE THINKS THAT YOU'RE
GOING TO STEAL KAGOME AWAY.
- SAVE IT!
- OWWW!
- TRUE AS THAT MAY BE,
YOU'RE NOT HELPING.
- YOU REALLY NEED TO GROW UP,
MUTT FACE.
- YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU
WHERE NARAKU LIVES?
IF I KNEW THAT,
I WOULDN'T BE WASTING MY TIME
BATTLING HIS DEMONS.
- DOES THAT MEAN YOU DON'T KNOW?
- IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE
TO FIND.
NARAKU'S PROJECTED A BARRIER
AROUND HIS CASTLE.
LET US AVENGE THE DEATH
OF YOUR COMRADES.
ALL I ASK IS THAT YOU HAND OVER
THOSE JEWEL SHARDS IN YOUR LEGS.
[GRUMBLES]
AND HIGHTAIL IT BACK
TO YOUR DEN!
- UHH.
SOMETHING THE MATTER, MUTT FACE?
YOU'RE SWINGING YOUR SWORD
AWFULLY SLOWLY.
[GRUNTS]
- THE TETSUSAIGA'S
STILL TOO HEAVY FOR HIM.
- AND IT WON'T GET
ANY LIGHTER OVERNIGHT.
- COME BACK AND FIGHT!
- SORRY, DOG BREATH,
BUT I DON'T HAVE ANY TIME
TO WASTE SPARRING WITH YOU
- COWARD!
COME BACK HERE!
- NOW, YOU TAKE GOOD CARE
OF MY KAGOME
WHILE I GO WASTE NARAKU.
DON'T YOU DARE
LAY A FINGER ON HER.
- WHAT?
- HE SURE IS COCKY
FOR A GUY WHO
JUST RAN AWAY FROM A BATTLE
COME ON, INUYASHA.
NOW DON'T GET SO RILED UP.
[GRUMBLES]
- WHO SAID I WAS RILED UP?
[SIGH]
- HIS JEALOUSY
IS FLATTERING, SURE,
BUT I WOULDN'T MIND
IF HE WAS A BIT NICER.
YOU'RE EXHAUSTING.
- HUH?
YOU MEAN YOU REALLY ARE TIRED
OF BEING WITH ME?
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
ALL DEPRESSED FOR?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT WHAT
KOGA TOLD YOU, INUYASHA.
- HE'S MORE CONCERNED ABOUT
WHAT YOU TOLD HIM, KAGOME.
- MM-HMM.
- HMM?
[GRUNTS]
- HUH?
WHAT IS THAT?
[BUZZING]
- LOOKS LIKE INSECTS.
- WAIT, KOGA!
- THIS IS THE SAME SCENT
AS KAGURA'S.
NO MISTAKING IT.
UHH.
THE YOUNG LEADER
OF THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE.
YOU PICKED UP MY SCENT
EVEN BEFORE INUYASHA.
- I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE NARAKU!
THE SCENT IS
IDENTICAL TO KAGURA'S.
HE MUST BE NARAKU.
YOU SLAUGHTERED MY COMRADES
AND NOW I WILL
AVENGE THEIR DEATHS!
- AAH!
[LAUGHS]
- PITY FOR YOU,
BUT I'M AFRAID YOU SHALL BECOME
FODDER FOR MY NEW INCARNATION.
- A CAGE?
HA.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF FEAST YOU BROUGHT,
BUT THE TIMING
COULDN'T BE BETTER.
I'LL GLADLY GET REVENGE
FOR MY MEN.
[LAUGHS]
- KOGA, MEET YOUR OPPONENTS.
EMERGE FROM YOUR CAGE, JUROMARU.
[GROWLING]
- WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH HIM?
HAVE IT YOUR WAY, NARAKU.
I'LL TAKE HIM OUT FIRST.
THEN I'LL MASH YOU BOTH
INTO THE GROUND.
WHAT'S THE HOLDUP HERE?
HURRY AND RELEASE HIS SHACKLES
SO I CAN GET MY HANDS ON HIM.
- NO.
HE'LL BE ENOUGH OF
A CHALLENGE FOR YOU
JUST AS HE IS.
[GRUMBLES]
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S HIS FUNERAL!
UHH.
DIE!
UHH!
[GRUNTS]
ARGH!
GET OFF ME!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
HE'S FAST.
MAYBE EVEN FASTER THAN ME.
WAIT.
WHAT'S THAT CHILL IN THE AIR?
IT'S COMING FROM THAT
BIT IN HIS MOUTH.
[GRUMBLES]
- I CAN SMELL NARAKU!
- WAIT UP, INUYASHA!
- DON'T GO RUNNING OFF
ON YOUR OWN!
INUYASHA, YOU'RE NOT EVEN
STRONG ENOUGH
TO WIELD THE TETSUSAIGA YET!
- SPARE ME!
IT'S MORE THAN
JUST NARAKU'S SCENT.
THE STENCH OF THAT NASTY KOGA'S
COMING THROUGH, TOO.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S GOING
TO BRING NARAKU DOWN.
I WON'T LET THAT MANGY WOLF
GET HIM FIRST!
- UHH! UHH!
- KOGA!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
LEAVE ME ALONE!
CAN'T YOU SEE I'M BUSY?
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- HUH?
HOW'D HE CATCH UP WITH ME?
- OHH!
UHH.
NICE JOB ESCAPING
AS USUAL, KOGA.
HE'S GONE.
HUH?
- UHH.
- YOU'VE FINALLY SHOWN UP,
HAVE YOU, INUYASHA?
- NARAKU!
- KOGA MUST'VE FLED WHEN HE SAW
HE HAD NO CHANCE OF VICTORY.
HA HA.
HE'S MORE INTELLIGENT
THAN I TOOK HIM FOR.
- HUH.
WHO CARES ABOUT HIM?
I'M IN A WHOLE DIFFERENT
CLASS ALTOGETHER.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
IS THAT ANOTHER OF
NARAKU'S INCARNATIONS?
- JUROMARU.
I SHALL REMOVE YOUR SHACKLES.
GO FORTH AND FIGHT
TO YOUR HEART'S CONTENT.
- HUH?
[GASPING]
WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?
- HA HA HA HA.
JUROMARU IS UNSTOPPABLE
NOW THAT HIS MASK
HAS BEEN REMOVED.
HE WILL SLAUGHTER
EVERYTHING IN HIS WAKE.
[EXHALES]
- I DON'T LIKE THE LOOKS
OF THIS JUROMARU.
HE MAKES MY SKIN CRAWL.
- EVEN IF NARAKU
WAS A DEMON PUPPET,
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT
HE JUST BEHEADED HIS OWN ALLY.
- PERHAPS NO ONE IS HIS ALLY.
- THAT WOULD EXPLAIN WHY NARAKU
KEPT HIM SHACKLED AND BRIDLED.
[EXHALES]
- UHH!
UHH!
- WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?
HE DIDN'T EVEN TRY
TO DODGE MY ATTACK.
IS THIS A TRAP?
NO, THAT DEMON'S ALL BRAWN.
HE COULDN'T THINK UP
COMPLEX BATTLE PLANS.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
FINISH YOU OFF HERE AND YOU.
UHH.
IRON REAPER SOUL--
- HE BLOCKED IT.
- UHH!
AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- UHH.
UHH.
HOW THE HELL?
DID HIS ARMS JUST GROW?
CAN HE TRANSFORM OR SOMETHING?
- DID YOU FIND NARAKU?
- YEAH.
HOW COME YOU CAME BACK?
- DON'T TELL ME YOU RAN AWAY.
- HA.
NO CHANCE.
THAT NARAKU BROUGHT ANOTHER
STUPID-LOOKING SIDEKICK
ALONG WITH HIM.
- THAT GUY GAVE ME
A BAD FEELING,
AND I'VE LEARNED
TO TRUST MY INSTINCTS.
I BET INUYASHA WISHES
HE'D DONE THE SAME.
HE'S PROBABLY GETTING
BEATEN TO A PULP BY JUROMARU
AS WE SPEAK.
YOU MEAN YOU SAW INUYASHA?
- YUP.
- HUH?
- UH, KOGA?
I COULD BE OUT OF LINE
FOR SAYING THIS.
- IF HE'S IN DANGER
AND KAGOME'S WITH HIM,
DOESN'T THAT PUT HER
IN DANGER AS WELL?
- AAH!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
THAT EARLIER, YOU CLOWNS?
- WHY DIDN'T YOU
NOTICE IT FIRST?
- UHH.
[GRUNTING]
GOT YOU!
- GOOD ONE!
- HE CUT THE DEMON'S ARM OFF!
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHY DIDN'T I FEEL HIS ARM SEVER?
IT'S ALMOST LIKE IT
SEPARATED FROM JUROMARU.
HUH?
- AAH!
UHH!
- HUH?
- HIS ARM'S STILL ON.
I KNEW IT.
THAT WASN'T HIS ARM
I HACKED OFF.
- AAH!
- LOOK!
FROM THE GROUND!
- INUYASHA!
[GROANING]
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT THING?
- THANKS FOR THE MEAL.
YOUR INNARDS
WERE SIMPLY DELICIOUS
- DAMN IT!
SO THERE WERE
2 OF YOU ALL ALONG.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- HA HA HA HA.
I AM KAGEROMARU.
AND I HAVE BEEN LYING DORMANT
INSIDE JUROMARU'S BELLY.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
OH NO!
DON'T TELL ME THAT--
- THAT BIT SEEMS TO BE
THE ONLY THING THAT WAS
KEEPING IT INSIDE.
[LAUGHS]
- JUROMARU OBEYS NO ONE BUT ME.
NOT EVEN NARAKU.
- WHAT?
- NOW LET US FEAST
ON THE OTHERS,
SHALL WE, JUROMARU?
WE'LL GORGE OURSELVES!
- WIND TUNNEL!
[LAUGHS]
- UHH!
WHAT THE?
- MIROKU!
HIRAIKOTSU!
UHH!
UHH.
SANGO!
UHH!
[LAUGHS]
- WIND TUNNEL!
- WHAT ARE YOU
HOPING TO ELIMINATE?
- OVER THERE!
- TOO LATE.
- HUH?
- DO YOU HONESTLY
HOPE TO DEFEAT US
WITH SUCH SLUGGISH SPEED?
- AAH!
- UHH.
MIROKU!
[GRUNTING]
MIROKU.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- YEAH.
YOUR SWORD SCARED ME
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
- PULL UP THE COVERS
AND DON'T WATCH THIS PART.
HE'S MINE THIS TIME.
- NO!
DON'T DO IT, INUYASHA!
- YOU'VE GOT A HOLE IN YOUR GUT,
FOR STARTERS!
- SO WHAT?
IT'S NOT LIKE I'VE
NEVER BEEN WOUNDED--HUH?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- THIS GIRL'S LIFE
BELONGS TO ME NOW.
- KAGOME!
- UHH!
- HUH?
- KAGOME, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- WHERE'D YOU COME FROM?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE PULLING HERE, DOG FACE?
HOW DARE YOU PUT
MY KAGOME IN DANGER!
- WHO ARE YOU TO TALK,
RUNNING OFF WITH YOUR TAIL
BETWEEN YOUR LEGS?
I WILL THANK YOU
FOR SAVING KAGOME, THOUGH,
YOU MANGY WOLF.
- ARE THEY SAYING I WAS
IN SOME KIND OF DANGER?
- SEEMS LIKE.
- SO WHAT'S THE STORY BEHIND
THIS STRANGE-LOOKING DEMON?
- HE CAME OUT OF JUROMARU'S GUT,
OR SO HE CLAIMS.
- FIGURES.
NO WONDER I WAS SENSING
A CHILL FROM JUROMARU.
IT WAS HIM.
- I CAN SEE THAT KAGEROMARU
IS MUCH TOO FAST
FOR EVEN THE LIKES OF US
TO KEEP UP WITH HIM.
- HA!
WHY DON'T YOU SPEAK
FOR YOURSELF, MONK?
THERE'S NO ONE WHO'S CAPABLE OF
ESCAPING FROM ME.
- HA HA HA HA HA.
WORDS ARE YOUR ONLY TRUE WEAPON.
- I'LL CALL YOU ON THAT ONE,
AFTER I TWIST YOUR HEAD OFF.
- HA HA HA HA.
YOU'RE NOT HALF THE WARRIOR
YOU CLAIM TO BE.
IS THAT TRULY
THE BEST YOU CAN OFFER?
PFFFT.
- JUROMARU, I'M YOUR ONLY
REAL OPPONENT HERE!
- UHH!
[GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA!
- HUH!
SHAME ON YOU, MUTT FACE.
THAT LAME EXCUSE FOR A DEMON
SHOULD BE EASY PREY.
- WHAT?
UHH.
GET OFF ME.
WHO ARE YOU TO CRITICIZE?
I DON'T SEE KAGEROMARU
LYING FACE DOWN.
- HA.
DON'T COMPARE YOURSELF TO ME.
HUH?
HUH.
I'M STARTING TO GET
THE HANG OF THIS.
YAAA!
[GROWLING]
I'VE GOT YOU.
HUH!
- HE'S PREDICTING
KAGEROMARU'S MOVES.
- THAT'S UNREAL.
[GROWLS]
- HUH!
- UHH!
- YOU'RE DEAD!
- GOT HIM!
- HUH?
HE'S GONE.
HE GOT AWAY ON ME.
HUH?
- UHH!
- HUH?
HE CAME OUT OF THE GROUND!
- UHH!
[GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA!
- HE GOT AWAY ON ME AGAIN!
[GRUNTS]
- HUH?
-NO.
THERE'S NO WAY HE'LL EVER WIN
WITH AN INJURED LEG.
- AND INUYASHA'S
STILL UNCONSCIOUS.
- HA HA HA.
PERHAPS I SHOULD EAT YOUR LIVER
NEXT, LITTLE GIRL
[SCREAMS]
- WHAT?
- KAGEROMARU!
DON'T LAY A HAND ON HER!
- I'LL EAT HER, BONES AND ALL!
- OHH!
- NO, YOU WON'T!
- UHH!
- HUH?
- TOO LATE!
[SCREAMING]
UHH.
- INUYASHA!
- NOW, DIE!
- WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
DID THE SWORD
JUST BECOME LIGHTER?
HE WIELDED TETSUSAIGA
WITH ONE HAND.
- HE'S SO SIMPLE-MINDED
THAT WHEN HE GOT ANGRY,
HE FORGOT HOW HEAVY
THE SWORD WAS.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- SIMPLE-MINDED, HUH?
HE HEARD THAT?
IS HE UNDERGROUND?
- INUYASHA.
KAGOME, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I AM,
BUT YOU'RE SERIOUSLY HURT.
- UHH!
SO DOG BREATH
IS STILL ALIVE, IS HE?
- KOGA'S LEG HAS BEEN
BADLY INJURED.
- HMPH.
LIKE HE'D BE ANY USE TO ME.
STAND BACK AND WATCH THE MASTER.
I'LL TAKE JUROMARU OUT
BY MYSEL--
[CRASH]
- TETSUSAIGA GET HEAVY AGAIN?
- IT WAS HIS DESIRE
TO PROTECT KAGOME
THAT MADE THE SWORD
SEEM LIGHTER.
- UHH.
- COWARD.
LOST YOUR NERVE, HUH?
- SPARE ME.
[GRUNTING]
I'LL FINISH YOU OFF
WHILE I'M AT IT.
AHH!
- UHH!
- YOU'RE A DEAD MAN!
UHH!
- YAAA!
- UHH!
- YAA!
- DON'T EXPECT A "THANKS."
- YOU'RE SUCH AN INGRATE.
UHH.
- UHH--
- IF THIS BATTLE
GOES ON MUCH LONGER,
NOT EVEN INUYASHA
WILL BE ABLE TO HOLD OUT.
- AND THERE'S NO WAY OF KNOWING
WHERE KAGEROMARU
WILL EMERGE FROM NEXT.
- WAIT.
INUYASHA WILL HAVE A CHANCE
IF WE CAN RESTRAIN KAGEROMARU.
MIROKU, GIVE ME
YOUR STAFF, PLEASE.
- WHY?
WHAT DO YOU HAVE PLANNED?
- WATCH.
THIS POISON WON'T LAST
VERY LONG,
BUT AT LEAST IT'LL GET
KAGEROMARU OUT OF THE GROUND.
UHH!
- THE EARTH'S
STARTING TO TURN RED.
- HMM.
- YAAA!
- IT WORKED.
- NOW CAPTURE KAGEROMARU.
HE'S GOING TO BE SLOWED DOWN
BY THE POISON.
- UHH.
DAMN YOU.
- UHH!
YOU'RE MINE NOW.
[GRUNTING]
- OHH!
- UHH.
- THAT WAS JUST GREAT, DOG BOY.
YOU GONNA DIE THIS TIME AROUND?
- INUYASHA!
DON'T MOVE AROUND.
- DON'T WORRY, KAGOME.
I CAN HANDLE BOTH DEMONS
ON MY OWN.
NOW THAT KAGEROMARU CAN'T DO
HIS LITTLE UNDERGROUND TRICK,
I'LL TAKE HIM OUT.
BUT YOU'RE GOING DOWN FIRST.
- WHY CAN'T I SENSE KAGEROMARU?
IS HE HIDING
IN THE SHADOWS SOMEWHERE?
[GASP]
- I KNOW WHERE HE IS.
[EXHALES]
- FOOL!
STAY AWAY FROM HIM, KOGA!
- TAKE YOUR OWN ADVICE,
WHY DON'T YA!
[GRUNTING]
- DON'T GO.
YOU'RE TOO WEAK.
- OUT OF THE WAY.
[EXHALES]
- MOVE OR IT YOU'RE GOING DOWN
WITH THOSE DEMONS.
- SEAL NOW.
- WHAT?
- YOUR FATE IS SEALED NOW.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT!
UHH!
- HUH.
[SCREAMING]
- OH!
- NOTHING BUT ASHES.
- HE DID IT.
- IT'S OVER, DESPITE SOMEONE
GETTING IN MY WAY.
UHH!
- YOU THIEF!
WERE YOU ACTUALLY
GOING TO KILL ME TOO?
THAT'S A GOOD ENOUGH ANSWER
FOR ME.
- THERE YOU GO.
- I'M GONNA WASTE YOU.
- KNOCK IT OFF, YOU GUYS.
- NOTHING'S SACRED TO YOU
WHEN YOU'RE SWINGING
THAT THING AROUND,
IS IT, DOG BOY?
- HE KNOWS HOW FAST YOU ARE,
SO HE WAS SURE YOU'D
GET OUT OF THE WAY IN TIME.
RIGHT, INUYASHA?
- WHY SHOULD I EXPLAIN MYSELF
TO THAT MANGY WOLF?
LISTEN, IF YOU EVER
GET IN MY WAY AGAIN,
NEXT TIME, I REALLY WILL
KILL YOU.
- I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU TRY IT,
YOU LAME EXCUSE FOR A HALF-DOG.
- PARDON?
- INUYASHA, SIT.
- UHH!
[CRASH]
KOGA, MAYBE YOU BETTER
LEAVE US FOR NOW.
- WOULD YOU STOP DOING THAT?
- YOU'VE GOT SOME
SERIOUS INJURIES.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT'LL HAPPEN
IF YOU KEEP FIGHTING LIKE THIS?
HEY, KOGA, THANKS FOR
ALL YOUR HELP TODAY.
YOU KNOW, WE REALLY COULDN'T
HAVE DONE IT WITHOUT YOU.
- OK.
NOW HE'S DEFINITELY
NOT GONNA WANT TO LEAVE.
- KAGOME, YOU'RE MY WOMAN NOW.
MAN, I HATE LEAVING YOUR SAFETY
IN THE HANDS OF THAT
INCOMPETENT DOG FACE.
[SIGHS]
- THAT CREEP.
HE'LL PAY FOR THIS.
- I WILL ALWAYS
COME TO YOUR RESCUE
WHEN YOU'RE IN DANGER.
FAREWELL.
- HUH?
- HE LEFT HER.
- GET BACK HERE, YOU COWARD!
- SIT, BOY.
- UHH!
YOU LET KOGA GET AWAY AGAIN.
[SIGHS]
- YOU'RE JUST TOO BANGED UP,
I TELL YA.
- DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
THAT MANGY WOLF COULD DEFEAT ME?
- HMM.
[SIGHS]
- NOW, TURN OVER,
AND LET ME DRESS YOUR WOUNDS.
- I'LL PASS.
ANYWAY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING,
FLATTERING HIM WITH
ALL THAT SWEET TALK,
AND EVEN FLIRTING WITH HIM?
DON'T DENY IT.
I HEARD YA.
- YOU'RE SO DISGUSTING.
I COULDN'T EVEN BEAR TO WATCH.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ABOVE ALL--HUH?
[WHIMPERING]
- WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT ME
LIKE THAT FOR?
- I'M GOING HOME.
- HUH?
- HOME TO MY ERA.
- GO AHEAD.
I'M NOT STOPPIN' YA.
- UGH.
SHALL WE, SANGO?
THIS IS GOING DOWNHILL FAST.
- YEAH.
I'D RATHER BE DRESSING
YOUR WOUNDS, FOR ONE.
- HUH?
- YOU TWO SHOULD GROW UP
AND BE LIKE THEM.
- HUH?
HMPH.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- NARAKU, WHO HAD KILLED KIKYO
50 YEARS AGO,
RETURNS TO RID THE WORLD OF HER
ONCE AGAIN.
INSIDE NARAKU, ONIGUMO'S HEART
CONTINUES TO BEAT,
AND IT YEARNS FOR KIKYO,
LEAVING NARAKU HIMSELF
BURNING WITH ANGER.
WITH KIKYO IN DANGER,
INUYASHA CAN'T HELP BUT
GO TO HER RESCUE.
BUT WHY DOES HE HAVE
TO EMBRACE HER LIKE THAT?
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!