>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING
FOR OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND
FORMS BETWEEN US.
>> A NEW HOPE.
A BRIGHT FUTURE BEGINS NOW.
>> THERE IS ONLY ONE WAY TO
DEFEAT THE WICKED NARAKU.
GATHERED HERE ARE KIKYO, NARAKU,
INUYASHA, AND THE REST OF US
WHOSE FATES ARE INTERTWINED.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
INUYASHA.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
>> HUH?
>> AAH!
CORPSES OF THE PARASITE
CHRYSALIS.
>> DAMN. UHH.
>> SO. THE RUMORS AMONGST
THE VILLAGERS WERE TRUE.
>> THEY SAID THAT 7 DAYS AGO,
THE MOUNTAIN DISAPPEARED
OVERNIGHT.
YOU THINK IT HAD SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE PARASITES?
>> IT'S FAINT, BUT I'M STILL
PICKING UP THE SCENT OF NARAKU.
>> NARAKU?
>> YEAH. THAT AND THE
STENCH OF DEMONS.
THE SOIL HERE'S DRENCHED IN IT.
IT REEKS OF DEMONS.
>> [GRUNTING]
DAMN.
NO MATTER HOW MANY I KILL,
THEY KEEP ON COMING.
HMM?
SO, DID YOU FIND THE NEST?
>> KAGURA.
>> WHAT ARE THESE STRANGE
INSECTS, ANYWAY?
>> PARASITE CHRYSALIS.
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT, THOUGH.
THEY USE GIANT DEMONS
AS THEIR HOST.
THERE'S NO WAY THEY'D BUILD
NESTS OUTSIDE THEIR HOST.
>> YOU'RE AWFULLY FAMILIAR
WITH THEM.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU KNOW?
>> HUH?
>> DON'T PLAY DUMB.
WHY DID NARAKU ORDER US
TO KILL THE PARASITES AS SOON AS
WE FOUND THEM?
YOU MUST HAVE SOME IDEA,
DON'T YOU?
>> NO. I DON'T KNOW WHY.
[BUZZING]
>> HMM?
SAIMYOUSHOU.
THEY'RE TELLING US TO GO BACK.
COME ON.
YOU SURE YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING, KOHAKU?
>> UH...
>> NARAKU DOESN'T TRUST ME.
HE TRUSTS YOU.
>> HMM?
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
>> THAT WASN'T MY IMAGINATION.
THE MOUNTAIN MOVED JUST NOW.
>> OH, NO.
>> THE PARASITE CHRYSALIS
HAD NO PLACE TO GO, MEANING,
THEY COULDN'T LIVE INSIDE THE
LARGE DEMON ANY LONGER.
NARAKU MUST'VE ORDERED US
TO KILL THE PARASITE CHRYSALIS
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T WANT ANYONE
FINDING OUT ABOUT THE HOST.
A MOUNTAIN THAT MOVES.
COULD THAT BE THE HOST OF THOSE
PARASITE CHRYSALIS?
HUH?
KAGURA.
>> SHE HAS A BAD HABIT OF
WILLFULLY GOING OFF ON HER OWN.
>> THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
THAT MOUNTAIN IS ALIVE.
NARAKU.
WHAT'S HE GOT UP HIS SLEEVE
THIS TIME?
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DOES NARAKU KEEP SUCH AN
UNRELIABLE WOMAN LIKE KAGURA
ALIVE?
KOHAKU, NARAKU'S
GIVEN HIS ORDER.
GO AND HELP KAGURA.
>> HUH?
>> GO.
>> IT'S NEAR.
I SMELL A DEMON.
>> INUYASHA, LOOK.
THAT MOUNTAIN.
>> I-IT'S MOVING.
[WHIMPERING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> WHO ARE YOU? HUH?
>> UHH.
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU ONE OF NARAKU'S
HENCHMEN?
>> NARAKU.
NARAKU, YOU SAY.
THE VERY NAME OF THE FOOL
WHO ENTERED MY BODY
AND DISTURBED MY SLEEP.
>> WHAT?
NARAKU ENTERED THIS GIANT
DEMON'S BODY?
>> I WAS AWAKENED FROM MY
200-YEAR SLUMBER AFTER DEEPLY
INHALING HIS FILTHY AURA
AND MIASMA.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> HE STOLE THE PROTECTIVE STONE
FROM WITHIN MY BODY.
>> PROTECTIVE STONE?
>> WHERE IS NARAKU?
IF YOU'RE HIDING HIM,
YOU WON'T BE SPARED.
>> IDIOT. I AIN'T HIDIN' HIM.
WE'RE AFTER NARAKU, TOO.
UHH!
>> TELL ME WHERE NARAKU IS.
UNTIL YOU DO,
ALL WILL SUFFER MY WRATH.
>> I ALREADY TOLD YOU.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M LOOKING FOR NARAKU MYSELF.
UHH.
>> HANG ON A MINUTE.
YOU MENTIONED THAT NARAKU HAD
STOLEN YOUR PROTECTIVE STONE.
WHAT IS THIS PROTECTIVE STONE
YOU SPEAK OF?
>> A STONE THAT IS VITAL
FOR ME--GAKUSANJIN.
THE STONE MATCHES A BARRIER
THAT ALLOWS ME TO CONTINUE MY
SLUMBER UNDISTURBED.
THE FUYOUHEKI.
>> FUYOUHEKI?
>> MASTER GAKUSANJIN,
THE FUYOUHEKI IS THE STONE THAT
KEEPS YOU PASSIVE
AS A DEMON MOUNTAIN?
>> IT DISSIPATES MY DEMONIC AURA
AND KEEPS ENEMIES FROM
APPROACHING SO THAT I WILL NOT
ENGAGE IN UNNECESSARY BATTLES.
>> HIS DEMONIC AURA?
>> DISSIPATES IT?
>> IF NARAKU GOT HOLD OF THE
FUYOUHEKI, WOULD HIS DEMONIC
AURA DISAPPEAR?
>> HE MIGHT'VE TAKEN IT
SO HE COULD HIDE IT FROM US.
>> WHAT KIND OF SHAPE IS THIS
FUYOUHEKI THAT ACTS AS A
BARRIER FOR YOU?
WHAT COLOR IS IT?
DOES IT HAVE A SCENT?
>> WHY DO YOU ASK?
>> I'LL GET IT BACK FOR YOU.
>> I DO NOT TRUST YOU.
>> DO YOU ALWAYS WAKE UP IN
SUCH A BAD MOOD?
>> [GROWLING]
>> WINDSCAR! UHH.
>> [GROANING]
>> UHH.
>> [GROWLING]
>> HMPH.
WE AIN'T GONNA GET ANYTHING MORE
OUTTA HIM.
I GUARANTEE YA.
>> INUYASHA.
>> LET'S GO.
>> YOUNGSTER.
>> HMM?
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU KILL ME?
YOU COULD HAVE.
>> HUH.
DID YOU WANT ME TO KILL YOU?
>> INUYASHA.
>> HE HELD BACK BECAUSE THERE'S
NO SENSE IN FIGHTING YOU.
WE HAVE ONLY ONE ENEMY--NARAKU.
IF WE HAPPEN TO FIND THE
FUYOUHEKI ALONG THE WAY, WE WILL
RETURN IT TO YOU.
>> HAVEN'T HAD ENOUGH?
>> TAKE SOME.
>> WHAT ARE THEY?
>> CRYSTALS OF MY DEMONIC AURA.
>> HUH?
>> GRAB A FEW.
WHEN YOU ARE NEAR THE FUYOUHEKI,
THE AURA OF THE CRYSTALS
WILL DISAPPEAR.
IF YOU MOVE AWAY FROM IT,
THE AURA WILL REAPPEAR.
>> THIS WILL HELP IN LOCATING
NARAKU.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE GAKUSANJIN
HAS DECIDED TO TRUST US.
>> YES.
>> THANKS. THAT WILL HELP.
>> ENOUGH.
NOW GO.
>> I STILL DON'T GET IT.
WHAT'S NARAKU UP TO?
WHY DID HE STEAL SOMETHING
LIKE THE FUYOUHEKI?
>> MMF. WHAT'S HE GONNA USE
THE STONE FOR?
>> WE'RE ALREADY HAVING A
HARD ENOUGH TIME FINDING NARAKU,
SO WHY DOES HE STILL NEED
TO HIDE HIS DEMONIC AURA?
>> IT'S ALL STARTING TO MAKE
SENSE.
NARAKU IS GOING TO USE THE
FUYOUHEKI TO CAMOUFLAGE
THAT INFANT'S AURA
AND KEEP IT HIDDEN.
>> YOU MUST HURRY.
[BUZZING]
>> KANNA IS SUPPOSED TO BE
WITH THE INFANT.
I'LL FINALLY FIND IT.
KAGURA SAID THAT IF THE INFANT
IS FOUND, NARAKU CAN BE KILLED.
[BUZZING]
UHH.
YOU WANT ME TO KILL THEM?
>> UHH.
THE BLESSED LOCK OF MISTRESS
KIKYO'S HAIR IS UNRAVELING.
>> SOMETHING IS NEARBY.
AAH!
>> [GRUNTING]
SHIKIGAMA.
WHOSE ARE THEY?
UHH.
[GRUMBLING]
>> YOU ARE NARAKU'S SUBORDINATE?
>> I SENSE A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
THERE'S JUST ONE.
IT'S KOHAKU.
>> KOHAKU?
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
KEEPS YOU ALIVE.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
DOES NARAKU CONTROL YOUR LIFE?
>> UHH.
>> WHY DO YOU OBEY NARAKU?
I SENSE THAT YOUR SOUL IS--HMM?
UHH!
>> HUH.
THE DEMONIC AURA IS DISAPPEARING
FROM THE CRYSTALS GAKUSANJIN
GAVE US.
>> DOES THAT MEAN THAT THE
FUYOUHEKI IS UP AHEAD?
>> NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
>> THEN NARAKU MUST BE
THERE, TOO.
>> NOT ONLY THAT, I'M STARTING
TO SMELL KIKYO.
>> WE HAVEN'T MET IN FAR TOO
LONG, KIKYO.
NOT SINCE MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> NARAKU.
>> IT'S A SHAME.
I WAS CERTAIN THAT I'D FINALLY
KILLED YOU LAST TIME WE MET.
>> THINGS WON'T ALWAYS GO
THE WAY YOU EXPECT, NARAKU.
I DIDN'T NOTICE THAT HE WAS
STANDING RIGHT BEHIND ME.
I DIDN'T SENSE HIS PRESENCE.
EVEN NOW, I DON'T SENSE NARAKU'S
DEMONIC AURA.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
>> [CHUCKLES]
WHAT'S WRONG, KIKYO?
WEREN'T YOU EXPECTING ME?
>> UHH.
UHH!
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> I CAN'T REACH MY NEXT ARROW.
>> WHAT ARE YOU STARING AT,
KOHAKU?
HURRY UP--TAKE KIKYO'S HEAD.
>> [GRUMBLING]
>> MM.
>> ARE YOU RELUCTANT
TO OBEY ME, KOHAKU?
>> [GRUMBLING]
UHH.
>> KOHAKU!
>> SISTER.
>> I CAN'T SENSE NARAKU'S
DEMONIC AURA.
THE FUYOUHEKI'S POWER
IS INCREDIBLE.
>> HUH?
KIKYO.
DAMN YOU, NARAKU!
>> HMPH.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> I'LL PURIFY HIM.
>> UHH.
NARAKU!
HE GOT AWAY.
>> HUH.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I WAS CARELESS.
I DIDN'T SENSE NARAKU'S
DEMONIC AURA.
>> HE MUST'VE STOLEN THE
FUYOUHEKI IN ORDER TO COME AFTER
YOU.
>> FUYOUHEKI?
>> A PROTECTIVE STONE THAT MAKES
DEMONIC AURAS DISAPPEAR.
>> HMM.
>> IT'S ODD, THOUGH.
IF LADY KIKYO WAS ACTUALLY
WHO HE WAS AFTER, THEN NARAKU
SEEMED UNUSUALLY CASUAL
ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH. GOOD POINT.
>> KOHAKU.
>> SAY, KAGOME,
THEY'RE AT IT AGAIN.
YOU OK WITH THAT?
>> LADY KIKYO IS NOT LIKELY
TO TRAVEL WITH US.
THIS IS NOTHING NEW.
THEY'RE PROBABLY SAYING THEIR
GOOD-BYES LIKE ALWAYS.
>> SURE TAKING LONG ENOUGH.
>> YOU CAN'T BLAME THEM.
WE'RE ALWAYS WITH INUYASHA,
BUT NOT KIKYO.
>> MAN. I WISH HE'D WRAP IT UP.
>> I WONDER WHAT THEY'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> SO ARE YOU SAYING NARAKU
IS A DIVERSION?
>> I'M CERTAIN OF IT.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
MY SHIKIGAMA WERE CLOSE TO
DISCOVERING SOMETHING.
>> WHAT WAS IT?
>> IT SEEMS THAT NARAKU DID NOT
DIE BY MY ARROW.
>> YEAH.
EVER SINCE MOUNT HAKUREI,
HE WON'T DIE, NOT MATTER HOW
MANY TIMES I DESTROY HIS BODY.
>> THAT CAN ONLY MEAN THAT HIS
HEART IS LOCATED SOMEWHERE ELSE.
>> HIS HEART?
SO THAT'S WHAT HE'S TRYING TO
HIDE WITH THE FUYOUHEKI?
>> IN ORDER TO DESTROY NARAKU,
I MUST FIND HIS HEART.
>> KIKYO.
>> THIS FUYOUHEKI WILL MASK
YOUR DEMONIC AURA.
THE PREVIOUS OWNER SAID THAT HE
USED IT TO KEEP HIM FROM
SENSELESS FIGHTING.
[CHUCKLES]
SO, HOW WILL YOU USE IT?
>> LOOK, KOHAKU.
HUMAN SOULS.
>> HUMAN SOULS?
>> SO MANY OF THEM WERE EATEN.
THE DEMON HAKU ATE THEM.
LET'S HUNT HIM DOWN.
SLIT OPEN HIS BELLY.
TAKE CARE THAT YOU DON'T DAMAGE
HIS STOMACH.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING
SHINY INSIDE.
WHAT IS IT?
>> THAT'S THE HAKU--
THE HUMAN SPIRIT.
>> THE HAKU?
>> THE LIVES OF THE PEOPLE
HE ATE.
>> THIS IS DISAPPOINTING.
I THOUGHT THAT SINCE WE HAD
THESE CRYSTALS THAT SENSE AURA,
WE COULD CATCH UP
TO NARAKU EASILY.
>> AND IT'S NARAKU'S HEART
WE'RE AFTER.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT KIKYO TOLD ME.
>> HEY, INUYASHA,
IS THAT ALL YOU TALKED TO
KIKYO ABOUT?
>> THAT'S ALL.
>> IF THAT'S TRUE, THEN THEY
DIDN'T HAVE TO GO OFF ALONE
LIKE THAT.
LOOKS SUSPICIOUS.
>> HUH?
[GRUMBLES]
>> YOU COULD CUT THROUGH
THIS AIR WITH A KNIFE.
>> THAT'S NOTHING NEW.
JUST GRIN AND BEAR IT.
>> HMM?
I SMELL A DEMON.
HMM?
>> CORPSES OF DEMONS
SCATTERED EVERYWHERE.
>> HUH?
>> [GROWLING]
>> WHAT THE HELL KIND OF DEMON
IS THAT?
>> [GROWLING]
>> [SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
>> [GROANING]
>> WHAT WAS IT?
>> LOOKS LIKE A COMPILATION
OF A NUMBER OF DEMONS.
>> LOOK--THAT'S THE
SOUL OF A DEMON.
>> NOT QUITE.
THOSE ARE THE HAKU.
ALL HUMANS, ANIMALS, AND DEMONS
HAVE WITHIN THEM THE HAKU
AND CONE SPIRITS.
CONE IS THE HEART OR SOUL,
AND HAKU IS THE POWER
TO ANIMATE THE BODY.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THE CONE
SPIRIT OF THIS DEMON?
>> IT WAS PROBABLY RELEASED
WHEN IT DIED, SO ONLY THE HAKU
KEPT THE DEMON MOVING.
>> HMM.
IN OTHER WORDS, AS LONG AS
THE HAKU EXISTS, EVEN A DEAD,
SOULLESS BODY CAN MOVE?
>> YOU THINK NARAKU
IS INVOLVED SOMEHOW?
>> THE CORPSES OF THE DEMONS
ARE SCATTERED IN 4 DIRECTIONS.
>> MAYBE THIS DEMON ISN'T THE
ONLY ONE WITH A HAKU THAT
KEEPS HIM MOVING.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER.
>> AAH!
>> [SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY]
>> [INDISTINCT]
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> [GROWLING]
>> [SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY]
>> HMPH.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, INUYASHA?
>> I COULD SMELL 'EM.
THERE'S LOTS OF 'EM.
>> AAH!
>> [GROANING]
>> AHH!
>> INUYASHA! BEHIND YOU!
>> ANOTHER ONE, HUH?
WINDSCAR!
>> [GROANING]
>> THESE DEMONS ARE STARTING
TO LOOK MORE AND MORE HUMAN.
>> DEFINITELY.
COMPARED TO THE EARLIER ONES,
IT'S ALMOST LIKE--
>> EXACTLY.
IT'S AS THOUGH THE EARLIER
DEMONS WERE ALL EXPERIMENTAL
VERSIONS.
>> HUH?
THE SCENT.
HAKUDOSHI'S NEARBY.
>> WELL, WELL.
YOU SNIFFED ME OUT, DID YOU?
>> HMPH.
HAKUDOSHI, WHAT KIND OF DIRTY
TRICK YOU GOT PLANNED THIS TIME?
>> HMPH.
WHY DON'T YOU ASK
MORYOUMARU HERE?
>> WHAT?
>> LOOK AT THAT DEMON.
>> THEY ARE GETTING CLOSER AND
CLOSER TO HUMANS,
JUST AS WE THOUGHT.
>> I CREATED MINI-DEMONS AND
TESTED THEM ALL.
THEN I REALIZED THAT IT'S
EASIER TO MAKE THEM MOVE
WHEN THEY'RE FORMED LIKE HUMANS.
WITH HUMAN HAKU, HUMAN FORMS
WORK BEST.
>> SO, THIS IS ALL YOUR DOING?
>> MORYOUMARU, GO AHEAD AND
FIGHT INUYASHA.
>> DON'T TELL ME HE'S GOING TO
TEST THAT THING OUT ON INUYASHA.
>> SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
YOU'RE ON.
I'LL USE YOUR LITTLE DEMON
TO PRACTICE MY NEWEST
TECHNIQUE ON.
>> MORYOUMARU.
>> HMPH.
ADAMANT BARRAGE!
HUH. GONE.
GUESS I OBLITERATED THE GUY.
>> ABOVE YOU!
>> HUH? UHH.
UHH. WHAT?
IT'S GOT WINGS?
>> [CHUCKLES]
WHY THE BIG SURPRISE?
I CREATED MORYOUMARU FROM
VARIOUS DEMONS, AFTER ALL.
MAKING HIM FLY WAS EASY.
>> HUH.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M SURPRISED?
ALL HE DID WAS FLY AWAY
TO DODGE MY ATTACK.
IT'S NOT LIKE HE DEFLECTED
MY ADAMANT BARRAGE.
YAH!
ONE MORE TIME SHOULD DO IT.
ADAMANT--UHH.
UHH.
>> INUYASHA!
>> HE'LL BE DEVOURED BY THE
REMAINS OF MORYOUMARU!
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> UHH. UHH.
DEVOURED? I DON'T THINK SO.
JUST TRY IT.
[GRUNTING]
ADAMANT...
BARRAGE!
>> HE BROKE AWAY.
[GASP]
UHH! AAH!
>> YOU SEE THAT?
HAKUDOSHI PROTECTED IT.
>> UHH. UHH.
HUH?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> UHH.
>> MIROKU!
>> UHH. IT'S OK.
I'M NOT HURT.
HE SURE OUTSMARTED US THIS TIME.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> HE STOLE THE CRYSTALLIZED
DEMONIC AURA FROM ME.
>> WHAT?
>> THE FUYOUHEKI WAS OUR WAY TO
FIND NARAKU.
I'M SO ASHAMED.
>> THE MAIN THING IS THAT
YOU'RE NOT HURT, MIROKU.
>> KAGOME'S RIGHT.
THERE ARE OTHER WAYS TO
FIND NARAKU.
>> MORYOUMARU BOTHERS ME,
THOUGH.
>> YES.
HAKUDOSHI PUT HIMSELF AT RISK
TO PROTECT HIM.
>> HE WENT OUT OF HIS WAY
TO STOP THE DEMON
FROM BEING DESTROYED.
>> AS YOU REQUESTED, I STOLE
THE CRYSTALLIZED DEMONIC AURA.
I AM LEAVING MORYOUMARU HERE.
USE HIM AS YOU PLEASE.
>> MORYOUMARU...
I WILL PUT A SOUL INSIDE YOU.
>> [MUSIC]
>> KIKYO AND SESSHOMARU
BOTH SEARCH FOR NARAKU.
IF WE'RE GOING TO DESTROY
NARAKU, WE HAVE TO FIND HIS
HEART.
>> KAGURA BETRAYS NARAKU
AND GUIDES US TO WHERE HIS
HEART IS HIDDEN.
>> BUT WE'RE LED RIGHT INTO A
DEMON'S BELLY.
>> YOU WILL DISSOLVE INSIDE THE
DEMON, LEAVING ONLY THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD.
>> WILL WE LIVE OR DIE?
THIS COULD BE OUR FINAL BATTLE.
NEXT TIME,
"THE BOND BETWEEN THEM,
USE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD!"
>> PLEASE, KAGOME,
HELP ME HANG ON!