>> KILL NARAKU?
>> YES, MOTHER.
NOTHING GOOD HAS COME OF MY PACT
WITH HIM.
I'VE HAD NOTHING BUT
INTERFERENCE.
MY PURPOSE WAS TO GATHER HUMAN
BLOOD TO DILUTE THE POISON IN
YOUR BODY, BUT IT'S BECOME
INCREASINGLY DIFFICULT.
MOST ANNOYING ARE THESE
DISTRACTIONS.
HOW COULD THEY DRAW ME, PRINCESS
AVI, INTO THIS?
SUCH PETTY FIGHTS BETWEEN HALF
DEMONS.
>> I SEE.
THEN YOU MUST ATTACK THE CASTLE
AND DESTROY IT.
>> A CASTLE?
>> YES, THERE IS A VERY
SUSPICIOUS CASTLE.
I'M CERTAIN IT'S CONNECTED IN
SOME WAY TO NARAKU.
>> BUT MOTHER, DO YOU MEAN--
>> I NOTICED IT ABOUT THE TIME
THAT ST. AGIRI APPEARED.
>> THAT PERSON!
AFTER THEM!
>> UHH! UHH!
THE BIRDS ARE AFLAME!
AAH!
>> UHH!
>> AGIRI THE HOLY ONE HAS
RETURNED.
>> HURRY! PLEASE SAVE US!
>> THE ONE WHO ERECTED THE
BARRIER.
SLAY HIM!
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
UHH!
>> LOOK, LOOK!
WE'RE SAVED!
>> MY BIRDS HAVE ALL BEEN SLAIN!
HOW ON EARTH COULD THIS
HAVE HAPPENED?
[THINKING]
EVER SINCE NARAKU CAME INTO
THE PICTURE, I'VE HAD NOTHING
BUT INTERFERENCE.
UHH!
>> IT SEEMS THAT ST. AGIRI IS A
HINDRANCE TO NARAKU.
HOW?
NARAKU'S DEMONS HAVE SCOURED THE
SKIES IN SEARCH OF ST. AGIRI'S
WHEREABOUTS.
I USED OUR BIRDS TO SPY ON THEM.
THERE WAS ONE SPOT THAT THE
DEMONS WOULD NOT APPROACH.
IT WAS A HUMAN CASTLE.
[BIRD SQUAWKS]
NARAKU'S DEMONS FLEW OVER IT
WITHOUT EVEN BOTHERING TO
LOOK THERE.
THE DEMONS HAD NO NEED TO CHECK
THIS PLACE, BECAUSE THERE IS A
CONNECTION BETWEEN THE CASTLE
AND NARAKU.
ATTACK THIS CASTLE AND FIND OUT
WHAT NARAKU IS HIDING IN THERE.
>> MY LADY.
MY LADY, THE YOUNG HEIR IS
SLEEPING VERY PEACEFULLY.
>> GOOD. I'M VERY GLAD.
>> HE SLEEPS RIGHT THROUGH THE
NIGHT, TOO.
SUCH A FINE YOUNG BABE HE IS.
IT'S AS THOUGH THAT FRIGHTFUL
NIGHT NEVER HAPPENED.
THE NIGHT I GAVE BIRTH TO THIS
CHILD, EVERYONE WHO ATTENDED ME
IN THE BIRTHING ROOM DIED.
AND IF THAT WEREN'T ENOUGH,
THOSE STRANGERS APPEARED.
I CAN'T REMEMBER ANY MORE THAN
THAT.
AND WITH EACH PASSING DAY,
MY MEMORY OF THAT NIGHT FADES.
HUH?
>> NARAKU! WAIT!
>> HUH?
>> YOU CANNOT COME IN HERE.
>> YOU THERE.
>> OH, MY LADY.
PLEASE, ACCEPT MY HUMBLEST
APOLOGIES.
THE YOUTH HAS ONLY RECENTLY COME
TO APPRENTICE UNDER ME.
HE KNOWS LITTLE OF THE WAYS OF
THE CASTLE.
IT IS ALL RIGHT, BUT PLEASE, LET
ME SEE THE BOY'S FACE.
RAISE YOUR HEAD, YOUNG MAN.
>> HUH?
>> HAVE I MET YOU SOMEWHERE
BEFORE?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
A HIGH-BORN LADY LIKE YOU WOULD
NEVER CROSS PATHS WITH THE LIKES
OF HIM.
RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> I SEE.
I MUST HAVE BEEN MISTAKEN THEN.
YOU MAY GO.
>> YES, MY LADY.
>> THE LADY OF THE CASTLE SEEMS
LIKE A VERY NICE PERSON.
>> SHE IS.
WE'RE ALL SO HAPPY SHE'S BORNE
AN HEIR.
IT'S A VERY GOOD OMEN.
>> AHH...
>> KOHAKU.
YOU AND KANA WILL STAY AT THIS
CASTLE.
>> YES.
>> LIVE IN THE CASTLE AND
PROTECT THE INFANT.
>> HMM?
>> KOHAKU, YOU MUST EAT MORE.
>> THANKS, I WILL.
HUH?
>> HERE. I'LL HAUL THESE
AWAY FOR YOU.
>> OH, I CAN TAKE CARE OF THAT.
>> IT'S NO PROBLEM.
[THINKING]
>> THIS CASTLE IS SO PEACEFUL.
I HAVE A FEELING THAT A LONG
TIME AGO I USED TO LIVE WITH
PEOPLE LIKE THIS.
PROBLEM IS, I DON'T REMEMBER
WHEN.
>> YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
BIRDS THAT SUCK HUMAN BLOOD.
DO YOU KNOW OF THEM?
>> OH, YES, THERE'S BEEN A HUGE
UPROAR ABOUT THEM.
I'VE HEARD ALL KINDS OF RUMORS
LATELY.
>> HAVE THEY BEEN SEEN IN THIS
AREA?
>> NOT THAT I'M AWARE OF.
AND BESIDES, WE'RE SO CLOSE TO
THE CASTLE.
>> HMM?
>> THERE'S NO WAY DEMONS WOULD
COME HERE.
>> I DON'T THINK THIS IS
THE PLACE, EITHER.
>> WE'RE DOING ALL WE CAN.
I MEAN, WE DON'T KNOW WHERE THE
BIRDS' NEST IS.
>> I GUESS WE HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO FIND LODGINGS IN THIS VILLAGE
TONIGHT.
>> NO CHOICE?
AND WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
HEADED, MONK?
>> WHAT A HANDSOME MAN.
>> STAY AND HAVE A GOOD TIME
WITH US.
>> OH, YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW I
WOULD LOVE TO DO JUST THAT.
>> THERE HE GOES, AT IT AGAIN.
>> HE NEVER LEARNS.
>> SHEESH!
>> THAT KID HAGODOSHI HAS NO
HEART.
THAT'S WHY HE DOESN'T DIE, NO
MATTER HOW OFTEN HE'S TORN
APART.
WHERE IS HIS HEART?
>> KAGRA, TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE
THINKING ABOUT.
>> OH, LEAVE ME ALONE.
CAN'T I AT LEAST THINK TO MYSELF
ONCE IN A WHILE?
HMM?
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
BIRD DEMONS?
WHICH MEANS THAT MUST BE
PRINCESS AVI THE BIRDMASTER.
>> KAGRA, GO AFTER THEM NOW.
>> HMM?
>> SIMPLY KEEP AN EYE
ON THEM.
DON'T DO ANYTHING UNNECESSARY.
>> WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU MEAN BY
UNNECESSARY?
>> GET GOING.
>> HMM!
>> NARAKU'S INSECTS AGAIN.
HAVE THEY COME TO SPY ON US?
HA!
MAYBE THAT'LL TEACH THEM.
HMM...ISN'T THAT INTERESTING.
LOOKS LIKE THAT FEMALE DEMON HAS
TURNED ON NARAKU.
>> UHH...UHH...
>> HEY, KOHAKU.
KOHAKU.
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU WERE MOANING IN YOUR SLEEP.
>> ARE YOU OK, SON?
>> WERE YOU HAVING A NIGHTMARE?
>> YEAH, I GUESS.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR DREAM ABOUT?
>> I DON'T REALLY REMEMBER.
>> HERE, DRINK.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> FEEL A LITTLE BETTER NOW?
>> MMM.
>> THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
>> HAVE A GOOD DREAM THIS TIME,
LAD.
>> MMM.
[MAN SNORING]
>> THERE HE GOES AGAIN.
ONCE THAT FELLA STARTS SNORING,
IT'S REAL HARD TO FALL ASLEEP.
[THINKING]
>> EVERYONE HERE IS SO KIND.
>> HA HA HA!
AREN'T YOU GOING TO THANK ME?
>> HA! FOR WHAT?
>> I SALVAGED YOUR BROTHER'S
LIFE AFTER HE WAS FELLED BY
THOSE ARROWS AT THE CASTLE.
>> UHH!
>> KOHAKU, WHY ARE YOU
PROTECTING THAT DEMON NARAKU?
>> I'D ERASED ALL OF KOHAKU'S
MEMORIES OF YOU AND HIS FORMER
LIFE IN THE VILLAGE.
>> KOHAKU, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
NOW?
>> AHH, THAT FELT FANTASTIC.
SANGO, WHY DON'T YOU HAVE ONE,
TOO.
>> MM-HMM.
>> UH!
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
>> PRINCESS AVI'S BIRDS.
>> YEAH, AND THEY'RE HEADING FOR
THE CASTLE.
>> YOU MEAN, YOU FORGOT WHAT
YOUR PARENTS LOOKED LIKE,
KOHAKU?
>> MM-HMM.
>> DID THEY DIE IN BATTLE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THAT'S A SHAME.
I SUPPOSE IT'S A GOOD THING YOU
ENDED UP HERE WITH US IN THE
CASTLE.
>> MMM.
>> WE'RE ALL ONE BIG FAMILY
HERE, EVERYONE WHO WORKS HERE.
>> MMM.
[CRYING]
>> HUH?
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
>> OHH!
[MEN SCREAMING]
>> BIRD DEMONS!
GET BACK!
>> OHH!
>> AMAZING.
>> NO! KOHAKU!
>> DON'T COME OUTSIDE NO MATTER
WHAT.
UNDERSTAND?
>> KOHAKU.
>> HUH?
>> KOHAKU, PROTECT THE INFANT.
>> OH.
>> I'M WORRIED, MY LADY.
>> DON'T BE, BECAUSE AFTER ALL,
MY BABY IS SAFE HERE WITH ME.
EVERYONE IN THE CASTLE WILL
PROTECT US,
EVEN IF IT COSTS THEM THEIR
LIVES.
>> THE BIRDS FINALLY SHOWED UP,
HUH?
>> THE CASTLE IS UNDER ATTACK.
I SENSE A JEWEL SHARD.
>> YOU DO?
>> JUST THE ONE, AND IT'S
KOHAKU'S SHARD.
>> HE'S AT THE CASTLE?
>> I'M POSITIVE.
IT'S GOTTA BE HIM.
[THINKING]
>> KOHAKU, HAS NARAKU ORDERED
YOU THERE?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO THIS
TIME?
>> KOHAKU, PROTECT THE INFANT.
>> FIRE!
PROTECT THE CHILD!
>> HAVE THE DEMON BIRDS
DISCOVERED THAT THE INFANT IS IN
THE CASTLE?
>> WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> YOU'RE THE NEW APPRENTICE,
AREN'T YOU, KID?
GO AND HIDE YOURSELF
SOMEWHERE, QUICKLY!
>> YES, SIR.
[THINKING]
>> THEY'RE PROTECTING ME.
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
>> SANGO, LISTEN, WHEN WE GET
TO THE CASTLE, YOU GO STRAIGHT
TO KOHAKU, OK?
>> RIGHT.
>> I'LL HANDLE THOSE BIRDS.
GET GOING, SANGO!
HURRY!
>> THANKS.
I SENSE THE SHARD OVER THAT WAY.
>> HEMOLAH.
KOHAKU.
>> [SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
>> INUYASHA!
NOT YOU AGAIN.
>> PRINCESS AVI.
YOU'LL STOOP TO ANYTHING, WON'T
YOU?
>> INUYASHA, I THOUGHT YOU WERE
NARAKU'S ENEMY.
WHY ARE YOU PROTECTING THIS
CASTLE?
>> WHAT?
THIS CASTLE?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY, THAT
THIS IS WHERE NARAKU'S HIDING?
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE TO FIND
OUT.
SO FAR, THOUGH, THE ONLY
RESISTANCE I'VE SEEN HAS COME
FROM THE HUMANS.
>> WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
>> I THOUGHT YOU AND NARAKU HAD
SOME KIND OF DEAL GOING ON.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
HE'S THE ONE WHO CAME TO ME FOR
HELP.
SO YOU CUT YOUR TIES WITH
NARAKU.
THEN STAY OUT OF MY WAY AND STOP
INTERFERING.
WE'LL DESTROY NARAKU OURSELVES.
>> I'LL DESTROY HIM AFTER I'M
DONE WITH YOU.
>> STAY OUT OF THIS!
[THINKING]
>> ONE GOOD THING THAT CAME OUT
OF MY PACT WITH NARAKU IS THE
BARRIER OF THIS FORKED TRIDENT.
>> DAMN YOU!
HUH? [INDISTINCT]
>> INUYASHA!
>> THERE'S ONE MORE THING IT CAN
DO.
HAAAA!
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
[THINKING]
>> THERE'S NO WAY THAT NARAKU
PLANNED TO HAVE PRINCESS AVI AND
INUYASHA FIGHT.
DOES THAT MEAN THERE'S SOMETHING
IN THAT CASTLE?
[BIRDS SHRIEKING]
>> THE BIRDS ARE ALL ON FIRE.
>> THE CASTLE'S ON FIRE.
MY LADY!
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO NOW?
[BIRD SQUAWKS]
>> MY LADY, PLEASE HURRY
OUTSIDE.
YOU'LL ALL BURN TO DEATH IF YOU
STAY HERE.
>> I'VE SEEN YOU BEFORE.
YOU'RE THE BOY NAMED KOHAKU.
>> I SAID HURRY!
>> HURRY?
BUT THERE ARE DEMONS OUTSIDE.
>> SHE'S RIGHT.
THERE ARE.
>> I MUST PROTECT MY BABY FROM
THE DEMONS.
HE'S THE PRECIOUS HEIR TO OUR
ESTATE.
>> DON'T BE AFRAID.
I PROMISE TO PROTECT THE INFANT
WITH MY LIFE.
NOW HURRY.
THIS WAY.
QUICKLY!
>> I CAN'T BREATHE.
>> JUST A LITTLE FURTHER.
>> MY LADY!
OUR YOUNG LORD?
>> THEY'RE ALL SAFE.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> THIS YOUNG BOY RESCUED US.
>> THIS BOY DID?
>> KOHAKU, THANK YOU FOR SAVING
US.
>> HUH? SURE.
>> WE MUST TAKE THEM AWAY TO
SAFETY RIGHT NOW.
>> KOHAKU, I WANT YOU TO STAY BY
OUR LADY'S SIDE.
>> RIGHT.
>> HERE THEY COME.
>> AAH!
>> I OWE YOU ONE, KOHAKU.
>> THAT WAY!
EVERYONE, HURRY!
>> RIGHT.
>> HEY, KID, TELL ME.
WHERE DID YOU LEARN TO FIGHT
LIKE THAT?
>> JUST BY WATCHING, I GUESS.
>> YOU'RE JUST LIKE A
DEMONSLAYER.
>> HUH?
>> HERE THEY COME!
WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU, LAD.
>> OK.
[THINKING]
DEMONSLAYER?
>> GO!
AAH!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I CAN ALMOST REMEMBER FIGHTING
LIKE THIS A LONG TIME AGO,
FIGHTING ALONGSIDE MY
COMRADES.
>> RUN FOR IT!
>> WHY, YOU!
>> HALF DEMON!
>> OUR LORD!
OUR LORD HAS BEEN SLAIN BY A
BIRD DEMON!
>> THE CASTLE HAS FALLEN.
>> KOHAKU.
>> IT'S ALL OK.
DON'T WORRY.
EVERYTHING WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> KOHAKU.
TAKE THE INFANT.
KILL EVERYONE IN YOUR PATH.
KILL.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T LET US DOWN, BOY.
>> I'M WORRIED, MY LADY.
>> YES, I KNOW, BUT I'M SURE
WE'LL BE RESCUED.
>> KOHAKU, WHERE ARE YOU?
[BIRD SQUAWKS]
>> YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD, KOHAKU.
>> YOU'RE A BIG HELP.
>> KOHAKU.
>> KILL THEM.
KILL EVERYONE AROUND YOU.
KILL THEM.
[MUSIC]
>> WHO AM I, ANYWAY?
>> KOHAKU HAS LOST HIS MEMORY
AND IS BEING CONTROLLED BY
NARAKU.
>> WHO'S SHE?
>> AND WHEN THEY MEET AGAIN, HE
CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER HIS OWN
SISTER SANGO.
>> YOU DID IT AGAIN, DIDN'T YOU?
>> AGAIN?
>> WHILE PRINCESS AVI AND
INUYASHA CONTINUE THEIR BATTLE,
SANGO AND KOHAKU CONFRONT EACH
OTHER AND THEIR TRAGIC PAST.
NEXT TIME, "THE CRUEL REUNION OF
FATE."
>> I WILL SEE THIS THROUGH,
EVEN IF IT COSTS ME MY LIFE.