>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS
BETWEEN US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> SERVED BY JAKEN...
>> LORD SESSHOMARU CONTINUES
HIS JOURNEY.
>> FAREWELL, LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> FAREWELL--
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> A FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
"INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> HMM?
>> WHAT COULD THAT BE UP AHEAD,
MASTER UNGAI?
>> LET'S FIND OUT.
>> [SCREAMING]
>> [LAUGHTER]
[GRUNTING]
HUH?
>> HUH?
>> [GRUNT]
>> HEY, YOU!
WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
[GRUNT]
DAMN YOU!
YOU WON'T GET AWAY.
KILL HIM!
[GROANING]
>> MASTER UNGAI, IT'S A DEMON.
>> HMM...
ARE YOU RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS?
STOP!
>> WHY SHOULD I?
I DON'T HEED HUMANS.
>> [GRUNT]
[GROANING]
THE DEMON MANAGED TO ESCAPE.
I WONDER WHO HE WAS.
I'VE NEVER FELT SUCH AN INTENSE
DESIRE TO KILL BEFORE.
>> MASTER UNGAI, THESE DEAD MEN
OUTSIDE THE VILLAGE SEEM TO BE
NIGHT ROBBERS.
>> MEANING THAT THE DEMON KILLED
THE BRIGANDS?
>> THEN WHICH OF THEM ATTACKED
THE VILLAGE?
>> ALL THE KIDS IN THE VILLAGE
WERE KIDNAPPED?
>> WHEN WE WOKE UP IN THE
MORNING, ALL OF THE CHILDREN OF
THE VILLAGE HAD VANISHED.
I HAD NO IDEA WHAT HAPPENED TO
THEM, WHETHER THE GODS OR EVEN
DEMONS SPIRITED THEM AWAY.
>> HEY, MAN, MY FRIENDS AND I
WILL FIND OUT WHERE THE CHILDREN
HAVE GONE.
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT A THING.
>> HUH?
>> WE MAY NOT LOOK LIKE WE CAN
ACCOMPLISH MUCH, BUT WE'RE
REALLY PRETTY GOOD.
>> WE'RE QUITE SKILLED WHEN IT
COMES TO SLAYING DEMONS.
AND IN RETURN FOR OUR HELP, ALL
WE WOULD NEED ARE LODGINGS.
>> JEEZ, YOU'RE NOT PULLING THAT
AGAIN.
>> THANKS, BUT WE DON'T NEED
YOUR HELP.
>> HUH?
>> I'VE ALREADY ASKED A MONK FOR
HELP.
>> OH...
>> YES?
AND YOU'RE LOOKING AT A MONK
RIGHT HERE.
>> I MEAN A GROUP OF MONKS WHO
SPECIALIZE IN VANQUISHING
DEMONS--THE MASTER UNGAI AND
HIS YOUNG ACOLYTES.
>> HMM?
>> I'M CERTAIN THAT HE AND HIS
SUBORDINATES WILL BE ABLE TO
RESCUE OUR CHILDREN.
>> MASTER UNGAI, YOU SAY?
SO, HE'S HERE.
HOW FORTUNATE.
>> HMM.
>> [GROANING]
I GOT IT!
>> YOU THERE.
>> HUH?
>> ARE YOU FROM THE VILLAGE AT
THE MOUNTAINFOOT?
>> MM-MMM.
>> HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
COME BACK!
I SENSE A DEMONIC AURA NEARBY.
COME BACK, I SAID!
HUH!
A DEMON, JUST AS I THOUGHT.
BUT WHO COULD THAT YOUNG GIRL
BE?
>> DID SOMETHING HAPPEN HERE,
MASTER UNGAI?
>> NO.
LET'S CONTINUE OUR SEARCH FOR
THE CHILDREN.
>> SAY, MASTER JAKEN?
>> YES?
>> AFTER HE DEFEATS NARAKU,
THEN WHAT DO YOU THINK LORD
SESSHOMARU IS GOING TO DO?
>> YOU PROBABLY DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THIS, BUT LORD SESSHOMARU HAS
LONG BEEN IN SEARCH OF PERSONAL
POWER.
HE WILL UNDOUBTEDLY BECOME THE
GREATEST DEMON OF ALL TIME AND
WILL REIGN OVER HIS OWN EMPIRE.
WHEN THAT HAPPENS, I WILL BECOME
THE EMPIRE'S CHIEF MINISTER.
HMM.
[SPITTING]
>> MASTER JAKEN?
>> HUH?
>> THIS EMPIRE OF LORD
SESSHOMARU'S, WHAT POSITION DO
YOU THINK I MIGHT HAVE IN IT?
>> HUH?
YOU MEAN YOU INTEND TO FOLLOW US
UP UNTIL THEN?
>> WHY, IS SOMETHING WRONG WITH
THAT?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU IS STRONG,
BUT WHO KNOWS HOW LONG IT WILL
TAKE TO CREATE THE EMPIRE?
TO US DEMONS, 100 YEARS IS
NOTHING AT ALL.
BUT TO A HUMAN LIKE YOU, TIME IS
EVERYTHING.
>> OH...
>> BY THE TIME THE LORD'S
EMPIRE'S CREATED, YOU'LL BE LONG
GONE.
>> HUH?
THAT WON'T HAPPEN.
I WON'T DIE.
>> [SNORING]
>> HUH?
[THINKING] STUPID MASTER JAKEN.
I'LL ALWAYS BE WITH LORD
SESSHOMARU.
FOREVER AND EVER.
[FLUTE PLAYING]
>> HUH?
RIN?
OFF TO PEE?
>> HMM.
>> WAIT, RIN.
RIN, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
RIN!
[MUTTERING]
HUH? SHE'S GONE!
>> THEY'RE ALMOST READY.
>> [CHIRPING]
>> HUH?
>> WHO ARE THEY?
>> MUST BE THOSE MONKS THAT SLAY
DEMONS, THE ONES THE HEAD MAN
TOLD US OF.
>> IT MIGHT NOT BE A GOOD THING
RUNNING INTO THEM LIKE THIS.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
>> I'VE HEARD MORE THAN MY SHARE
OF RUMORS ABOUT MASTER UNGAI.
THEY SAY HE'S UTTERLY RUTHLESS
WHEN HE DEALS WITH DEMONS.
>> HELLO. NICE NIGHT.
>> HMM.
>> [CHATTERING]
>> HMM?
YOU ARE DEMONSLAYERS.
>> YES, YOU COULD PUT IT THAT
WAY.
>> AND YET YOU KEEP A DEMON WITH
YOU.
VERY UNPRINCIPLED OF YOU.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> HMPH!
>> [CHATTERING]
>> IT'S AN EVIL SPIRIT WE'RE
DEALING WITH.
IF YOU RELY ON YOUR DEMON'S
HELP, YOU'LL ONLY REGRET IT.
>> NEITHER KIRARA NOR SHIPPO
WOULD HARM HUMANS.
I CAN PROMISE YOU THAT MUCH.
>> YOU HEARD THE LADY.
>> HMM.
>> [CHATTERING]
>> YOU ARE A PRIESTESS,
YOUNG LADY.
>> UH, YES.
>> THEN YOU SHOULD KNOW HOW
FRIGHTENING DEMONS CAN BE.
>> HA.
>> YOU THERE.
>> WHAT?
>> THAT'S A DEMON SWORD,
IS IT NOT?
>> HA.
YOU'RE GETTING ON MY NERVES.
>> INUYASHA...
>> SO WHAT IF IT IS A DEMON
SWORD?
>> YOU'LL BE KILLED IF YOU USE A
WEAPON THAT YOU CANNOT HANDLE.
>> IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
>> PERHAPS NOT.
BUT I WARN YOU, STAY OUT OF OUR
WAY.
>> ♪ NA NA NA NA NA
NA NA NA NA NA ♪
>> WHO DO THOSE GUYS THINK THEY
ARE?
TALK ABOUT ARROGANT.
>> I'M JUST GLAD THIS IS THE
NIGHT OF THE NEW MOON.
>> OTHERWISE, WE WOULDN'T HAVE
GOTTEN OFF SO EASILY.
YOU PROBABLY WOULD'VE HAD A
CONFRONTATION WITH THOSE MONKS.
>> HMM.
>> RIN! RIN!
RIN, WHERE ARE YOU?
RIN?
>> JAKEN.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
YOU'VE RETURNED.
>> DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO RIN?
>> WELL, FUNNY YOU SHOULD
MENTION THAT.
>> HMM.
>> SHE'S VANISHED, MILORD.
I THINK ONGOKUKI MAY HAVE
ABDUCTED HER.
>> ONGOKUKI, YOU SAY?
>> ONGOKUKI IS A DEMON WHO
LURES CHILDREN TO IT WITH THE
SOUND OF ITS FLUTE.
HE TAKES THE CHILDREN AND THEN
SELLS THEM TO OTHER DEMONS.
I HEARD THE SOUND OF ITS FLUTE
JUST AROUND THE TIME RIN
VANISHED.
MILORD, REST ASSURED THAT I WILL
FIND HER EVEN IF I NEED TO
TRAVEL TO THE END OF THE--WAIT!
LORD SESSHOMARU, WAIT FOR--
[MUTTERING]
OHH....
MY POSITION AS MINISTER IS
GROWING DIMMER BY THE MOMENT.
>> MMM...
[STRAINING]
>> [MOANING AND CRYING]
>> WHERE AM I?
INSIDE A CAVE?
CHILDREN?
TELL ME, WHO ARE YOU ALL?
AND WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> SO, YOU WERE KIDNAPPED BY THE
CREEPY DEMON, TOO.
>> WHAT DEMON?
>> WE'RE GONNA BE EATEN ALIVE.
>> I'M SO SCARED!
I WANT TO GO HOME!
>> MMM.
SHUT YOUR MOUTH, YOU LOUSY
LITTLE BRATS!
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE SCARED.
>> WE'VE GOT PLENTY TO BE
SCARED OF.
THAT THING'S A DEMON.
>> SO WHAT?
HE'S NOT SCARY.
>> HE'S AS SCARY AS THEY GET.
HE'S A DEMON!
>> BANDITS ARE A LOT SCARIER
THAN DEMONS ARE.
>> BANDITS?
A DEMON IS WAY SCARIER.
>> NOT EVEN CLOSE.
BANDITS GO AROUND KILLING PEOPLE
FOR NO REASON AT ALL.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
>> MY FATHER, MOTHER, AND
BROTHERS.
THEY WERE ALL BRUTALLY MURDERED
BY BANDITS.
>> YEAH, BUT A DEMON'S
OUR PROBLEM RIGHT NOW.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I KNOW HE'LL COME HERE TO
RESCUE ME.
>> WHO WILL?
>> HMM.
>> RIN!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
RIN!
>> SAY...
>> YES?
AAH! OH, IT'S ONLY YOU GUYS.
>> DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO RIN?
>> MM-HMM.
IT CERTAINLY HAS.
SHE WAS KIDNAPPED BY ONGOKUKI.
>> ONGOKUKI?
>> A DEMON WHO ABDUCTS CHILDREN!
HAVE YOU SEEN LORD SESSHOMARU?
HE WENT TO LOOK FOR RIN.
>> UH-UH.
>> OH...RIN!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> [GRUMBLING]
AHH.
[GRUMBLING]
[PLAYING HIGH-PITCHED NOTES]
WELL, WELL.
[GRUMBLING]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GROANING]
AAH!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GROANING]
>> EVIL DEMON, BE GONE!
>> [ALL SOBBING]
>> CHILDREN.
WE HAVE COME TO RESCUE YOU.
>> [ALL GASP]
>> YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
WE'VE TAKEN CARE OF THE DEMON.
>> [LAUGHTER]
>> THERE, THERE, MY BOY.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
IS THIS ALL OF YOU?
>> THERE'S ONE MORE GIRL
STILL INSIDE.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU AGAIN.
COME.
I'LL TAKE YOU BACK TO THE
VILLAGE.
>> I'LL BE FINE ALL BY MYSELF.
>> PUT ME DOWN!
LET GO OF ME NOW!
>> WHY DO YOU STRUGGLE FROM YOUR
SAVIORS?
>> SHE TOLD US THAT HUMANS ARE
WAY SCARIER THAN DEMONS.
>> WHAT?
HOW COULD YOU SUGGEST
SUCH A FOOL IDEA?
ANYWAY, YOU'D NEVER BE ABLE
TO SURVIVE ALONE
IN THESE MOUNTAINS.
>> SURE I CAN!
I CAN SURVIVE JUST FINE!
I CAN MAKE IT ON MY OWN.
>> I'VE HEARD ENOUGH FROM YOU,
STUBBORN LITTLE GIRL.
>> YOU LET ME GO, MISTER!
JUST YOU WAIT.
LORD SESSHOMARU WILL
COME FOR ME!
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, YOU SAY.
>> I NEVER WANT TO GO BACK TO A
VILLAGE TO LIVE WITH HUMANS.
LORD SESSHOMARU!
PLEASE HELP ME!
>> HMM?
>> UHH!
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
YOU CAME.
>> IT'S THE SAME DEMON
WE SAW THE OTHER DAY.
>> LET GO!
>> WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
HAVE YOU BEWITCHED
THIS YOUNG CHILD?
>> MASTER UNGAI.
>> HMM.
THIS DEMON'S FOUL AURA
MUST BE DEALT WITH.
HMM.
CHILDREN, HIDE IN THE CAVE
UNTIL I TELL YOU TO COME OUT.
>> [ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
>> WAIT FOR ME!
>> LOOK OUT, LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> UHH!
>> DEMON BE GONE!
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> HEY, WHAT WAS THAT SOUND?
>> I THINK UNGAI AND HIS MONKS
MUST BE FIGHTING.
>> WELL, THEY BETTER NOT TRY TO
USE SOME HALF-WITTED SPELL.
SESSHOMARU WILL KILL THE WHOLE
BUNCH OF 'EM.
>> MASTER, HE'S STILL ALIVE.
>> BE BRAVE, MEN.
IMMOBILIZE THE DEMON AT ONCE.
>> YES, MASTER.
>> ON!
EVIL DEMON, BE GONE!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> UHH!
>> [GROWLING]
>> HUH?
>> HE'S EXPOSING HIS TRUE SELF.
>> [GROWLING]
>> [GASP]
OHH! OHH!
>> AAH! UHH!
UHH!
>> UHH.
I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH
TERRIBLE POWER.
>> GRR. HUH?
>> RIN.
>> YES?
>> FOLLOW ME IF YOU SO CHOOSE.
>> YES.
>> HUH!
>> HUH? HUH?
>> DON'T GO.
HE IS AN EVIL SPIRIT.
HE IS A DEMON!
NOT SOMEONE A HUMAN CHILD
SHOULD FOLLOW.
>> LET ME GO!
>> COME BACK, GIRL!
HUMANS AND DEMONS LIVE IN
DIFFERENT WORLDS!
>> WAIT FOR ME.
>> BY THE TIME THE LORD'S
EMPIRE'S CREATED, YOU WILL BE
LONG GONE.
>> YOU KNOW I'M RIGHT.
NOW, LET'S GO BACK.
>> HA HA HA.
>> HUH?
>> WHY DID SHE GO?
WHY DID SHE LEAVE WITH HIM?
>> [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
HOW CAN WE EVER REPAY YOU?
>> IT'S NOTHING.
GOOD-BYE.
>> YOU GOT SOMETHING TO SAY
OR ARE YOU JUST HAPPY TO SEE ME?
>> YOU STUBBORN MULE.
COME ON--LOSE THE ATTITUDE,
WOULD YA?
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
WE WERE JUST TALKING.
>> IT'S THAT ATTITUDE THAT'S THE
PROBLEM HERE.
>> YOUNG WOMAN.
>> HUH?
>> PERHAPS YOU COULD
ENLIGHTEN ME.
WHY DO YOU STAY WITH A DEMON?
>> HUH?
>> FORGET IT.
IT'S NOTHING.
>> RIN.
UHH.
OH! OH!
OH! OH.
LORD SESSHOMARU.
UHH. LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> JAKEN.
>> HUH?
LORD SESSHOMARU!
OH, AND YOU, TOO, RIN!
>> WHERE IS AH-UN AT?
>> OH! [STAMMERING]
I'LL GET HIM.
I'LL GET HIM RIGHT AWAY.
>> [CHUCKLES]
HUH? HA HA HA!
UM, I WAS WONDERING,
LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> IF I DIED ONE DAY,
I WAS WONDERING, WOULD YOU--
WOULD YOU ALWAYS REMEMBER ME?
>> UH.
DON'T SAY SUCH SILLY THINGS.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
[MUMBLING]
UH, AND HERE'S AH-UN.
HUH? LORD SESSHOMARU.
WHERE ARE YOU--AAH!
>> DO YOU NEED TO ASK?
I'M GOING TO FIND NARAKU.
>> YES. OF COURSE YOU ARE.
MAY I COME ALONG?
I--I MEAN IF IT'S NOT TOO MUCH
TROUBLE OR ANYTHING. HMM?
>> YOU NEED TO ASK?
>> HUH?
>> OF COURSE YOU CAN COME,
MASTER JAKEN.
COME ON!
>> HUH? HOLD ON!
[LAUGHS]
>> [LAUGHS]
>> [MUSIC]
>> THE VILLAGE OF DEMON
SLAYERS--SANGO'S BIRTHPLACE.
NEARBY, KIRARA
MEETS UP WITH KOHAKU.
>> YOU WERE WORRIED ABOUT ME,
KIRARA?
THANKS.
I STILL CAN'T COME BACK, THOUGH.
>> KOHAKU HIDES THE FACT THAT
HE'S RETURNED TO NORMAL,
AND GOES AFTER NARAKU,
AND SANGO IS FULL OF AFFECTION
FOR HER BROTHER.
ONLY KIRARA KNOWS
HOW THE SIBLINGS FEEL.
NEXT TIME--KOHAKU,
SANGO, AND KIRARA.
THE SECRET FLOWER GARDEN.
>> KIRARA, WERE YOU
HERE WITH KOHAKU?