>> HYAH!
>> UNH!
>> FATHER, GIVE ME STRENGTH.
[GASPING]
>> THIS ORNAMENT MUST BE WHAT
CREATED THE BARRIER.
>> BUT THIS VAJRA WAS LOCKED UP
INSIDE THE TEMPLE.
>> IT CAN'T BE.
DOES THIS MEAN THAT SAINT
HAKUSHIN IS HELPING NARAKU?
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
TURNER ENTERTAINMENT GROUP]
[PANTING]
>> HEH.
THE BARRIER IS GONE, AND OUR
POWERS HAVE RETURNED TO NORMAL,
SO LET'S SETTLE THIS ONCE AND
FOR ALL, INUYASHA.
>> ERR.
[GROANING]
>> AT LEAST INUYASHA'S DEMONIC
POWERS ARE BACK.
>> ALTHOUGH HE IS STILL AT A
DISADVANTAGE.
HIS LEFT ARM IS BADLY INJURED.
>> INUYASHA, WILL YOU BE ALL
RIGHT?
BANKOTSU HAS TWO SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS IN HIS HALBERD, BANRYUU.
>> LET'S SEE YOU DO IT RIGHT
THIS TIME.
SHOW ME THIS WIND SCAR OF YOURS.
>> THANKS FOR THE INVITE.
[GRUNTS]
YOU'RE DEAD!
WIND SCAR!
>> UNH!
DRAGON HAMMER!
>> HE STOPPED IT.
>> HIS HALBERD STOPPED THE
ATTACK.
>> I JUST NEED TO LOOK FOR THE
WHIRLPOOL OF DEMONIC ENERGY.
THEN I CAN USE MY BACKLASH WAVE.
HUH?
WHAT?
I DON'T SEE A DEMONIC AURA
AROUND BANKOTSU, SO I CAN'T USE
MY BACKLASH WAVE?
>> DON'T STAND THERE IN A DAZE.
>> UNH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> HMM?
HMM?!
I FEEL LIKE A WEIGHT'S BEEN
LIFTED OFF MY SHOULDERS.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE FINALLY BACK
TO NORMAL, SHIPPO.
>> THE ONLY THING I CAN CLEARLY
REMEMBER IS THAT I STARTED
FEELING SICK.
>> YOU FAINTED BECAUSE OF THE
SACRED BARRIER SURROUNDING THIS
ISLAND.
IT SEEMS TO HAVE PURIFIED YOUR
DEMONIC POWERS.
>> THAT EXPLAINS IT.
OHH!
INUYASHA!
>> HE'S STILL UNDER ATTACK BY
BANKOTSU.
>> DAMN IT ALL!
>> HA HA.
IT SEEMS YOU HAD SOMETHING IN
STORE FOR ME.
TOO BAD IT WAS ALL IN VAIN.
>> DAMN!
>> INUYASHA, I KNOW YOU CAN DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
>> BANKOTOSU TOOK A GOOD SHOT AT
HIS ARM.
>> IS IT BAD?
[GROWLS]
>> KIRARA!
[ROARS]
THAT'S THE WAY, KIRARA.
TRY AND HELP INUYASHA!
HE WON'T LAST LONG WITH THAT
WOUNDED ARM.
>> BANKOTSU IS A SPECTER, BUT HE
WAS ONCE HUMAN.
JUDGING BY THE SCOPE OF HIS
STRENGTH, HE MUST BE USING SOME
KIND OF DEMONIC POWER.
>> THE BACKLASH WAVE TECHNIQUE
SURROUNDS AND REVERSES THE
NATURAL FLOW OF AN OPPONENT'S
DEMONIC AURA.
SINCE BANKOTSU WAS ONCE HUMAN,
HE DOESN'T PRODUCE ANY SUCH
AURA.
>> THE SACRED SHARDS OF THE
SHIKON JEWEL WANT ME TO DESTROY
YOU.
[GASPS]
>> THE BLACK LIGHT OF A TAINTED
SHARD!
[GASPS]
INUYASHA, BANKOTSU IS USING THE
POWERS OF THE JEWEL SHARDS IN
HIS HALBERD!
>> PERFECT!
NOW THAT I KNOW THAT, I CAN USE
MY BACKLASH WAVE.
>> HE'S THOUGHT OF SOMETHING.
I WON'T FALL FOR THAT AGAIN.
DO YOU ONLY HAVE ONE BATTLE
MOVE?
UNH!
>> HUH?
[BOTH GASP]
>> HE'S SUMMONED A THUNDERSTORM.
>> DAMN!
WHAT'S HE UP TO NOW?
>> AAH!
DRAGON THUNDER!
EVEN I CAN'T PREDICT WHERE THE
LIGHTNING WILL STRIKE.
>> LOOK AT ALL THOSE LIGHTNING
BOLTS!
>> HE CAN'T USE THE BACKLASH
WAVE!
>> AAH!
AAH!
>> WATCH OUT, SHINTARO!
>> KAGOME, COME BACK!
DON'T LEAVE THE BARRIER!
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME!
AAH!
>> AAH!
>> UNH!
[COUGHS]
HUH?
SANGO, SHIPPO, KIRARA.
KAGOME!
KAGOME?
[GRUNTING]
KAGOME!
[GRUNTS]
KAGOME.
HOW DARE YOU HURT KAGOME.
>> DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
I WAS TELLING THE TRUTH WHEN I
SAID I COULDN'T PREDICT WHERE MY
DRAGON THUNDER WOULD FALL.
YOU LIE THERE, LITTLE WORM.
I'LL HACK YOU AND YOUR SWORD TO
PIECES!
HYAH!
>> AAH!
[GRUNTING]
DAMN YOU!
THIS IS BETWEEN US!
WHY COULDN'T YOU KEEP MY FRIENDS
OUT OF IT?!
BASTARD, YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO GET
KAGOME AND THE OTHERS INVOLVED!
>> QUIT BEING SO NAIVE.
IT DOESN'T WORK FOR YOU!
YOU'RE DEAD!
HYAH!
>> HOW ABOUT SOME VARIETY?
THIS IS GETTING OLD.
UNH!
COME ON!
HOW MANY DIRTY, LITTLE TRICKS
ARE YOU GONNA TRY TO PULL ON ME?
>> ARE YOU STUPID?
IN A MATCH TO THE DEATH, THERE'S
NO SUCH THING AS FAIR OR FOUL!
>> UNH!
I'LL TAKE YOU DOWN EVEN IF IT
KILLS ME.
>> UNH!
>> HYAH!
[GRUNTING]
YOU'RE MINE NOW!
HYAH!
[GRUNTING]
>> OHH.
HUH?
>> HUH?
OHH!
>> SAINT HAKUSHIN'S ALTAR
ORNAMENT.
I KNEW IT.
>> HUH?
SAINT HAKUSHIN'S ORNAMENT.
THE DEMONIC AURA AROUND THE
TESSAIGA HAS BEEN PURIFIED.
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF THIS?
>> WAIT, INUYASHA!
THAT VAJRA WAS AT THE CORE OF
THE SACRED BARRIER AROUND THIS
ISLAND.
IT SEEMS SAINT HAKUSHIN IS AN
ALLY OF BANKOTSU.
>> OH, NO!
THAT CAN'T BE!
>> I TAKE IT HE WANTS ME TO
FINISH YOU OFF QUICKLY.
I HAVE TO ADMIT IT BOTHERS ME
THAT HE DOESN'T HAVE FAITH IN MY
ABILITY.
IT'S TOO BAD THIS HAS TO END SO
SOON FOR YOU ALL!
HYAH!
UNH!
>> HUH?
YOU GOT HIM, KAGOME!
>> OHH!
[BANKOTSU PANTING]
>> WELL, GIRL, YOU'LL REGRET
THAT.
>> YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A COWARD!
HUH?
>> OHH!
>> HIS ARM TURNED TO BONE.
>> A SACRED ARROW?
SHE MUST BE KAGOME, KIKYO'S
REINCARNATION.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT?
>> BANKOTSU IS...
>> DISAPPEARING!
>> BANKOTSU, DAMN YOU!
DON'T YOU DARE!
UNH!
[GROANING]
>> DON'T YOU DARE!
UNH!
A BARRIER!
[GRUNTING]
HE'S GONE!
>> INUYASHA!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I'M FINE, BUT NOW WHAT?
>> BANKOTSU ISN'T OUR ONLY
PROBLEM.
>> HMM?
>> THE VAJRA SEEMS TO HAVE
DISAPPEARED, AS WELL.
>> DO YOU THINK IT HELPED
BANKOTSU ESCAPE?
>> YES, PROBABLY.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT HAPPENED TO SAINT HAKUSHIN?
HE'S GONE.
WHERE DO YOU THINK HE COULD HAVE
DISAPPEARED TO?
>> HMM.
[COUGHING]
>> DAMN IT!
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED TO ME
ANYWAY?
WHERE AM I?
[FOOTSTEPS]
>> BANKOTSU, SIR.
>> KOHAKU, KANNA, WHERE ARE WE?
IT FEELS AWFUL IN HERE.
>> I IMAGINE THAT IT WOULD, SIR.
THIS ISN'T A VERY NICE PLACE FOR
MEN OF EVIL THOUGHTS.
>> IT DOESN'T SEEM TO BOTHER YOU
MUCH.
FIGURES, YOU BEING A NINJA.
>> YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
I'M NOT A NINJA.
>> HUH?
NOW I REMEMBER.
THE LIGHT FROM THE VAJRA
ENVELOPED ME.
HUH?
OH.
WHO IS THAT?
I SEE.
INUYASHA KEPT SAYING SOMETHING
OR OTHER ABOUT A SAINT.
THIS MUST BE SAINT HAKUSHIN'S
MUMMY.
HE'S RESPONSIBLE FOR CREATING
THE BARRIERS AROUND MOUNT
HAKUREI AND HIJIRI ISLAND.
>> FATHER'S GONE?
>> HE DIED PROTECTING THE
TEMPLE?
>> OHH.
SAINT HAKUSHIN DISAPPEARED FROM
THE ISLAND BECAUSE OF A DEMON
KNOWN AS NARAKU.
I BELIEVE FATHER DIED IN A
BATTLE WITH THIS DEMON.
>> POOR FATHER.
>> AT LEAST HE DIED HONORABLY.
>> OR FATHER'S BONES ARE IN
HERE.
>> OH, FATHER.
>> WE WILL GIVE HIM A PROPER
FUNERAL AND LAY HIS BONES TO
REST.
>> OH, HE'S NOT HERE!
>> WHERE IS HE?
>> WHAT TOOK YOU?
I'VE BEEN WAITING.
>> HUH? HEY, THERE, KOGA.
>> GREAT.
WE FINALLY CAUGHT UP TO HIM.
>> I CHASED THE THING ALL OVER
THE PLACE UNTIL EVENTUALLY IT
RAN IN HERE.
>> MEAT, MEAT, MEAT!
>> IT'S HUGE!
>> STARVING!
AAH!
>> YOU KNOW, THIS PLACE KIND OF
REMINDS ME OF HOME.
>> YEAH, BUT IT FEELS CREEPY.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE OF THE
BARRIER.
A BARRIER PROTECTS THE MOUNTAIN
SO DEMONS LIKE US CAN'T GET NEAR
IT, AND IT'S SO STRONG, IT EVEN
PERMEATES THIS CAVE.
>> MAN, THAT'S TAKING CAUTION
OVERBOARD.
>> WE LEAVE AFTER WE EAT.
>> HUH?
>> I'M POSITIVE THE BAND OF 7 IS
HIDING OUT SOMEWHERE INSIDE THIS
BARRIER.
I'LL FIND SOME WAY TO PASS
THROUGH IT.
>> GOOD-BYE, SHINTARO.
TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOURSELF AND
YOUR SISTERS!
>> I'LL PRAY FOR YOUR GOOD
JOURNEY!
>> IF FOR SOME REASON YOU EVER
FEEL LONELY, PLEASE DON'T
HESITATE TO CALL ON ME.
I'LL COME TO YOUR AID ANYTIME,
DAY OR NIGHT, ESPECIALLY
NIGHT--AAH!
AAH, AAH, AAH!
>> THAT'S ENOUGH OUT OF YOU,
MIROKU.
>> THAT'S ATTACHED, YOU KNOW!
>> GOOD-BYE.
TAKE CARE, ALL OF YOU!
>> WOW!
LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THIS VALLEY,
MASTER JAKEN.
HUH?
>> I STILL FEEL TERRIBLE, EVEN
THOUGH WE'VE COME A LONG
DISTANCE FROM MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> THE PURIFYING AURA THAT KEEPS
OUT ANYTHING DEMONIC EXTENDS ALL
THE WAY HERE.
NARAKU'S SCHEMES ARE AT THEIR
FINAL STAGES.
>> OHH!
SESSHOMARU!
OH, PHENOMENAL.
AAH!
SESSHOMARU!
>> AFTER HIM, AUN.
>> AAH!
HOLD ON, RIN!
DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND!
AAH!
OHH!
SLOW THIS THING DOWN, WOULD YOU?
I DON'T WANT TO FALL OFF!
AAH!
OHH!
>> STOP MAKING SUCH A FUSS,
MASTER JAKEN.
>> I CAN'T HELP IT!
AAH!
>> YOU'RE SO ANNOYING.
>> I CAN'T TAKE THIS!
AAH!
>> LADY KIKYO, DO YOU REALLY
HAVE TO LEAVE US?
>> FORGIVE ME.
I WANTED OT STAY LONGER.
>> FIRST, DR. SUIKOTSU LEFT, AND
NOW YOU.
>> AND NOW YOU'RE GOING TO
LEAVE.
LADY KIKYO, WE WERE ACTUALLY
HOPING YOU WOULD STAY HERE WITH
US FOR A WHILE, AT LEAST UNTIL
THE DOCTOR RETURNS.
>> YOU'RE STILL WAITING FOR HIM,
EVEN AFTER ALL THAT HAS HAPPENED
TO YOU?
>> YES.
DR. SUIKOTSU SUFFERED IN PAIN
SOMETIMES, BUT HE WAS VERY KIND
TO US.
>> THE VIRTUOUS SIDE OF SUIKOTSU
PROTECTED THESE CHILDREN, YET...
>> UH, IF YOU HAPPEN TO MEET
DR. SUIKOTSU, COULD YOU GIVE HIM
A MESSAGE?
PLEASE TELL HIM THAT WE'RE
WAITING FOR HIM.
>> YUTA.
>> HMM.
I'LL PASS THAT ALONG IF I SEE
HIM.
SUIKOTSU DISAPPEARED IN MOUNT
HAKUREI'S BARRIER.
YUTA, CHIO, THE SUIKOTSU YOU
KNEW NO LONGER EXISTS.
THE BARRIER HAS BECOME STRONGER.
I CAN'T TAKE IT MUCH LONGER
EITHER.
>> THE POWER OF THE BARRIER IS
BECOMING STRONGER.
[SHIPPO GROANING]
HUH?
WHAT?
>> I'M WORRIED.
THE BARRIER IS MAKING SHIPPO SO
DIZZY.
>> HEY, MIROKU, ARE YOU
ABSOLUTELY SURE THAT NARAKU IS
HIDING IN MOUNT HAKUREI?
>> I'M NOT ENTIRELY CERTAIN, BUT
I'M POSITIVE THAT SAINT HAKUSHIN
IS THE ONE CREATING THIS
BARRIER.
>> WELL, IT DOES MAKE SENSE
BECAUSE THE SAINT PROTECTED
BANKOTSU, ONE OF NARAKU'S MEN.
>> I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT A
MASSIVE EVIL LIKE NARAKU
WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO ENTER A
SACRED PLACE LIKE THAT.
>> ONCE INSIDE, THOUGH, THERE'S
NO BETTER PLACE TO HIDE.
THINK OF THOSE WHO HUNT HIM--THE
WOLF DEMON KOGA, SESSHOMARU,
YOU, INUYASHA, AND KIKYO ARE ALL
UNABLE TO GO TO MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> LET'S NOT WASTE ANY MORE
TIME, MIROKU.
>> RIGHT.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WE'VE DECIDED THAT SANGO AND
I WILL GO SURVEY MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> INUYASHA AND KAGOME, YOU STAY
HERE.
>> ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
THE TWO OF YOU ARE GOING THERE
ALONE?
>> WATCH OVER KIRARA.
I CAN'T TAKE HER.
>> YEAH, SURE, SANGO.
>> DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT A
THING, KAGOME.
FROM THIS POINT ON, I WON'T HAVE
A SPARE MOMENT TO CARESS SANGO'S
ENTICING BODY.
>> I'LL SHOW YOU ENTICING!
>> I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DO
THIS?
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT'S AT
MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> INUYASHA CAN'T GO IN PAST THE
BARRIER, REMEMBER?
IT HAS TO BE THE TWO OF US.
>> STILL...
>> SANGO, MIROKU, JUST CHECK
AROUND, BUT DON'T TAKE ANY
UNNECESSARY RISKS, OK?
>> REST ASSURED, THAT'S WHAT WE
INTEND TO DO.
>> WE'RE OFF.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
THINK THEY'LL BE ALL RIGHT?
>> WE DON'T REALLY HAVE MUCH
CHOICE EXCEPT TO HAVE FAITH IN
THEM.
>> THE BAND OF 7?!
>> THEY ALL DISAPPEARED?
>> THEY'VE TAKEN REFUGE ON MOUNT
HAKUREI.
DAMN IT!
GINKOTSU, RENKOTSU, GET OUT
HERE!
>> THIS IS BAD!
KOGA IS TRAPPED IN THE STEEL
THREADS!
>> IF HE GETS DRAGGED INSIDE,
HE'LL BE PURIFIED!
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA"...
>> "KOGA'S SOLITARY BATTLE."
>> WHERE ARE THEIR SHIKON JEWEL
SHARDS?