>> [GROWLS]
>> WE'RE BEING SUCKED IN.
>> PLEASE, KAGOME.
WE'VE GOT TO CONCENTRATE ON
KAGOME AND DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO SAVE HER FROM THAT DEMON.
>> ESPECIALLY WITHOUT
TETSUSAIGA.
>> ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE IF YOU
WANT IT BAD ENOUGH.
>> HA HA HA!
>> GRR...
>> NOTHING IN THE UNIVERSE LASTS
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
ALL SADNESS AND HAPPINESS FADES
WITH TIME.
EVEN THIS WORLD WILL SOMEDAY
SOON WILL BE DESTROYED BECAUSE
NOTHING LASTS FOREVER.
>> [YELLS INDISTINCTLY]
>> SO YOU SHOULD GIVE UP YOUR
SENSELESS STRUGGLE AND SURRENDER
TO YOUR INEVITABLE DEATH.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
AAH!
>> SAGA!
YAH!
>> YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND,
DO YOU?
YOU DON'T STAND ANY CHANCE OF
DEFEATING MY NAGINATA OF KENKON.
>> STOP!
THAT'S A LIE!
>> THE NAGINATA OF KENKON
IS INVINCIBLE!
>> AH!
>> OH, MIROKU!
OH!
UH!
>> BLADES OF BLOOD!
YAH!
UH!
>> [STRUGGLING]
>> YOU WANT THIS GIRL RETURNED
TO YOU SO BADLY.
>> [STRUGGLING]
>> YOU LOVE HER THAT MUCH,
DO YOU?
>> YES, IT'S TRUE.
I LOVE KAGOME.
>> HUH?
>> I WOULD GLADLY GIVE YOU MY
LIFE IN EXCHANGE FOR HERS.
PLEASE RETURN KAGOME.
>> HUH?
>> YOU SAID JUST NOW THAT
NOTHING LASTS FOREVER.
YOU'RE WRONG.
THERE IS ONE THING.
THERE'S LOVE, AND LOVE NEVER
DIES, NO MATTER HOW MUCH
TIME PASSES.
>> AKITOKI.
>> IMPULSIVE AS USUAL.
WHY DOESN'T HE KEEP HIS TRAP
SHUT AT TIMES LIKE THESE?
>> YOU WERE RIGHT ABOUT ONE
THING: IT IS TRUE I AM BUT A
WEAK HUMAN BEING.
YES, WE ARE SO WEAK, BUT THAT'S
WHAT MAKES US SPECIAL.
WEAKNESS!
IT'S OUR WEAKNESS THAT ALLOWS
HUMANS TO UNDERSTAND THE PAIN OF
OTHERS AND SHOW KINDNESS AND
COMPASSION TO EACH OTHER.
THAT'S WHY I BELIEVE THAT OUR
FEELINGS OF LOVE LAST FOREVER!
>> HRMPH!
FEELINGS, YOU SAY.
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
IF HUMANS HAD KINDNESS, IF THEY
TRULY DID UNDERSTAND PAIN, THEN
WHY DID TSUKIYOMI SEAL ME AWAY?
I CANNOT FORGIVE YOU.
WHAT HUMANS DID TO ME, I WILL
REPAY WITH DEATH, SO DIE KNOWING
HOW I FEEL!
>> OH!
>> HUH?
AH!
>> AH!
WHAT'S THIS?
BUT...YOU ARE...
IMPOSSIBLE.
[STRUGGLING]
>> WH-WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> THAT'S...
KAGOME?
>> KAGOME!
>> HOSHIYOMI.
>> AH...
TSUKIYOMI.
>> WE'RE FINALLY ABLE TO MEET
ONCE AGAIN...
HOSHIYOMI.
>> TSUKIYOMI, WHAT DO YOU WANT
WITH ME NOW?
>> I WANTED YOU TO THINK BACK
AND REMEMBER SOMETHING.
THE FEELINGS YOU ONCE FELT
TOWARD HUMANS LIKE ME, THE
KINDNESS YOU ONCE SHOWED ME,
AND THE MANY DAYS THAT WE SHARED
TOGETHER.
>> [GROWLING AND SCREECHING]
>> [PANTING]
ARE YOU HURT, TSUKIYOMI?
>> SAVE YOUR WORRIES
FOR YOURSELF.
I WON'T BE A DEAD WEIGHT,
HOLDING YOU BACK OR SLOWING
YOU DOWN.
>> HUH.
SO LIKE YOU.
>> DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN
RUN AWAY FROM US, FOOL?
>> YOU'RE NOT EVEN WORTH
FEARING.
>> YOU SURE GO TO GREAT PAINS
AND ALL FOR A MERE WOMAN!
ARGH!
LETTING A LOWLY HUMAN...
LETTING TSUKIYOMI STEAL
YOUR HEART.
>> YES, I EVEN CHANGED MY NAME
TO HOSHIYOMI.
THAT'S HOW MUCH I CARE
ABOUT TSUKIYOMI.
>> ARGH!
>> [SPEAKS FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> OH...
>> TSUKIYOMI!
YOU'VE USED TOO MUCH
OF YOUR STRENGTH.
IF WE CONTINUE HUNTING DOWN
DEMONS LIKE THIS, YOUR VERY LIFE
WILL BE IN DANGER.
>> IT'S TOO LATE TO GIVE UP
FIGHTING AT THIS POINT.
WE CANNOT STOP NOW.
THE DEMONS WHO BEGRUDGE US WILL
KEEP TRYING TO HUNT US DOWN.
>> NO!
THERE MUST BE A PLACE WHERE WE
NEED NOT FIGHT, SOMEWHERE WHERE
WE CAN LIVE TOGETHER IN PEACE.
>> HERE ARE THE CORPSES OF THE
DEMONS YOU SPOKE OF.
THERE ARE 222 OF THEM IN ALL,
AS YOU DEMANDED.
NOW YOU CAN COMPLETE THE
ULTIMATE WEAPON WHICH POSSESSES
THE POWER OF DARKNESS
AND LIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT, TSUKIYOMI, I ASKED
KAIJIMO TO FORGE THIS NAGINATA
OF KENKON IN ORDER TO FIND A
PLACE FOR YOU AND I TO LIVE,
A PLACE WITH NO FIGHTING.
I NEEDED A WEAPON THAT EQUALED
THE POWER YOU POSSESSED...
SO THAT YOU WOULD NOT NEED TO
EXPEND ANY MORE OF YOUR POWERS.
I DID IT ALL FOR YOU, TSUKIYOMI.
>> HOSHIYOMI.
>> WHY, TSUKIYOMI?
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO BETRAY ME?
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HA HA HA!
INCREDIBLE!
THIS WEAPON IS TRULY INCREDIBLE.
>> HOSHIYOMI.
>> BEHOLD, TSUKIYOMI, AS LONG AS
I HAVE THIS NAGINATA OF KENKON,
YOU WON'T NEED TO USE YOUR
POWERS ANYMORE.
>> AH...
>> OUR WORRIES ARE OVER.
EVEN IF A HUNDRED--NO, A
THOUSAND DEMONS--ATTACK US, I
SHALL BE ABLE TO PROTECT YOU.
>> HOSHIYOMI, THE NAGINATA OF
KENKON IS VERY DANGEROUS.
WE MUST SEAL IT UP AT ONCE!
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
TO LIVE IN PEACE WITHOUT HAVING
TO FIGHT, I MUST HAVE ABSOLUTE
POWER!
[THUNDER]
>> HOSHIYOMI IS BECOMING
POSSESSED BY THE NAGINATA
OF KENKON.
I MUST DO SOMETHING...
OR ELSE.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
[SPEAKS FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
>> TSUKIYOMI!
WHY?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
AAH!
[STRUGGLING]
TSUKIYOMI!
WHY?
>> [SIGHING]
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
AH!
SUCH TERRIBLE DEMONIC POWER!
EVIL POWERS, BE GONE FOREVER!
THE MISFORTUNE HAS NOW BEEN
SEALED.
AH...
MY DEAR HOSHIYOMI, I WILL
RELEASE YOU FROM THE SEAL NOW.
OH...
AH!
AHH...
[GASPING]
MY STRENGTH...
HOSHI...
YOMI...
[STRUGGLING]
[WIND]
>> TSUKIYOMI, YOU WERE
A MERE HUMAN.
THERE WAS NO WAY YOU COULD
LOVE ME, A DEMON.
IT WAS TOO MUCH TO HOPE FOR.
BUT THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
ARE YOU TELLING ME THE TRUTH?
>> I AM NOT SAYING THAT I DID
NOT BETRAY YOU, BUT I WANTED TO
SAVE YOU.
I WANTED TO RELEASE YOU FROM THE
SPELL OF THE NAGINATA OF KENKON.
THAT'S WHY I DID IT.
>> WAS IT ALL BECAUSE OF
MY OWN WEAKNESS?
WAS IT BECAUSE MY HEART DID
NOT HAVE FAITH IN TSUKIYOMI
THAT THIS DARKNESS WAS BORN?
>> HOSHIYOMI, MY BODY MAY NO
LONGER EXIST, BUT MY FEELINGS
FOR YOU WILL REMAIN FOR ALL
ETERNITY.
I LEAVE BEHIND NO REGRETS
IN MY PASSING.
>> RIDICULOUS.
RIDICULOUS!
HRMPH!
IT'S TOO LATE.
IT'S ALL FAR TOO LATE.
THE NAGINATA OF KENKON HAS
FINALLY BEEN RETURNED TO THIS
WORLD, AND IT THIRSTS FOR BLOOD
EVEN NOW!
>> KAGOME!
UH!
KAGOME!
SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
THE BLADE DIDN'T TOUCH HER.
KAGOME.
>> INUYASHA.
HUH?
LET ME DOWN.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
>> OK.
>> KAGOME?
>> I NOW POSSESS ABSOLUTE POWER.
I HAVE NO REGRETS WHATSOEVER.
I SHALL RID THE WORLD OF HUMANS
WITH THE NAGINATA OF KENKON.
>> ARE YOU STILL GOING ON
ABOUT THAT?
TSUKIYOMI DIED FOR YOUR SAKE.
SHE GAVE HER OWN LIFE FOR YOU.
HOW CAN YOU TOTALLY IGNORE HER
SACRIFICE?
>> KAGOME?
HUH?
THE TETSUSAIGA?
>> TSUKIYOMI WAS HUMAN ALL
RIGHT, BUT SHE WASN'T WEAK BY
ANY STANDARD.
SHE HAD A MUCH STRONGER HEART
THAN YOU EVER DID!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO BETRAYED
YOURSELF, HOSHIYOMI.
YOU BECAME BEWITCHED BY THE
NAGINATA OF KENKON'S TERRIBLE
POWER BECAUSE YOUR OWN HEART
WAS WEAK!
>> SILENCE, WENCH!
WHAT WOULD YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?!
>> AH!
>> DIE!
ARGH!
>> DON'T YOU DARE LAY A HAND
ON HER.
>> AH...
>> ARGH!
>> STAY AWAY FROM HER.
I PROTECT KAGOME.
>> DON'T YOU DARE LAY A HAND
ON HER.
>> ARGH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> YAH!
>> UH!
>> YOU'RE A DEAD MAN, HOSHIYOMI.
[STRUGGLING]
>> WINDSCAR!
>> YOU IMPUDENT HALF-DEMON!
>> WHAT?
>> MY POWER...
MY POWER HASN'T RETURNED YET.
>> HEH HEH.
YOUR SPIRITUAL POWERS HAVE ALL
BEEN ABSORBED BY THE NAGINATA
OF KENKON.
GIVE UP.
>> KAGOME!
>> THINK OF SOMETHING!
ISN'T THERE SOMEWAY TO HELP?
>> UH...
IF WE TAKE THE NAGINATA AWAY
FROM HIM, WE MIGHT STAND A SMALL
CHANCE, ALTHOUGH I COULDN'T
GUARANTEE IT.
>> TAKE HIS NAGINATA?
WE'LL BE KILLED WAY BEFORE WE
CAN STEAL IT.
>> OH, KAGOME...
>> OH...
>> MY BELOVED KAGOME IS FIGHTING
WITH EVERY DROP OF HER STRENGTH,
AND WHAT ABOUT ME?
>> AAH!
[STRUGGLING]
DIE!
>> AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
HUH?
>> UH, KAGOME.
YOU'RE SO DIFFERENT, SO SPECIAL.
>> HMM...
YAH!
>> AAH!
>> ARGH!
KAGOME, I ADMIT,
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU!
>> WHY YOU...
>> HUH?
OH, BROTHER.
THE DAMN FOOL.
>> UH!
>> YAH!
>> AAH!
>> I KNEW IT.
HUMANS ARE WEAK.
>> UH.
>> IF YOU WANT TO RUSH TO DEATH,
SO BE IT.
>> HELP ME OUT HERE, TSUKIYOMI.
>> DIE!
>> YAH!
>> STOP, HOSHIYOMI!
>> WHAT?
AH!
>> TSUKIYOMI, IT CAN'T BE.
>> AWESOME, MY POWER
HAS RETURNED.
>> GOOD THING AKITOKI WAS HERE
TO HELP, OTHERWISE, WE'D BE IN
TROUBLE.
>> I KNOW.
I OWE YOU BIG TIME FOR THIS,
HOJO.
>> UH.
DON'T MENTION IT.
HA HA!
>> NOW, WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PUT
AN END TO THIS GUY?
>> OK.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
[WIND]
HUH.
WHAT CAN YOU
POSSIBLY ACCOMPLISH?
EVERYTHING AND EVERYONE IS
POWERLESS AGAINST THE INVINCIBLE
NAGINATA OF KENKON.
>> HERE IT COMES.
>> YEAH.
>> BE GONE!
>> [YELLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[YELLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
>> HUH?
YAH!
IT'S BETTER THIS WAY.
THIS IS FOR THE BEST, RIGHT,
TSUKIYOMI?
AH!
>> UH.
>> KAGOME!
>> HUH?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, KAGOME?
>> HMM?
YEAH.
>> THAT WAS A FINE JOINT EFFORT,
I MUST ADMIT.
>> YOU TWO WERE IN PERFECT SYNC.
>> EXACTLY.
>> AH.
>> HE'S ME.
>> HUH?
>> HE WAS EXACTLY THE SAME WAY I
USED TO BE.
>> WHEN YOU SAY "HE," YOU MEAN
HOSHIYOMI?
>> YEAH.
THERE WAS A TIME WHERE I WAS
COMPLETELY POSSESSED BY MY OWN
DEMONIC POWER, AND I COULDN'T
EVEN CONTROL MYSELF.
HUH, IT'S EXACTLY THE SAME.
>> INUYASHA.
>> WELL, IT'S LUCKY FOR YOU
THAT YOU HAD KAGOME.
SHE EMBRACED YOU WITH KINDNESS
AND SAVED YOU.
>> YES, MANY TIMES.
>> THE FIRST NICE THING SHE DID
WAS TELL HIM TO SIT.
>> AH...
>> SHIPPO, HUSH.
>> COME TO THINK OF IT,
SHIPPO'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE NOT KIND,
NOT EVEN CLOSE!
>> WELL, I'M SORRY!
>> YOU SHOULD BE, YOU SCRAWNY
LITTLE PIPSQUEAK!
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> NOW, NOW.
THERE ARE DIFFERENT WAYS TO SHOW
ONE'S KINDNESS, REMEMBER?
>> AH, KAGOME, PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF.
>> ...I WON'T ARGUE ABOUT BEING
A LECHER, BUT HOW DARE YOU CALL
ME A FAKE!
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> I HAD DEEP FEELINGS FOR
KAGOME, FEELINGS THAT WOULD
NEVER FADE, EVEN THOUGH THEY
WOULDN'T BE RECIPROCATED.
HUH?
I BEG YOUR PARDON, MISS.
>> ARE YOU SPEAKING TO ME?
>> I AM.
MAY I ASK YOUR NAME?
>> MY NAME IS TSUSAKU.
>> TSUSAKU?
OH, I'D CHANGE THAT NAME
IF I WERE YOU.
IT DOES NOTHING FOR YOUR BEAUTY.
>> HUH?
>> CHANGE IT TO KAGOME.
THAT'S A LOVELY NAME.
NOW, THEN, HOW ABOUT WE CONTINUE
THE JOURNEY TOGETHER.
>> YOU ARE GOING THAT WAY,
THOUGH.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
LET US BE ON OUR WAY.
>> MY NAME IS AKITOKI HOJO.
I MAY LOOK YOUNG, BUT I'VE HAD
MY SHARE OF ADVENTURES.
WHY, JUST THE OTHER DAY...
>> HMM...
KAGOME...
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU, HOJO?
YOU'RE SURE ZONED OUT.
>> SITTING HERE FEELING SORRY
FOR YOURSELF WON'T GET YOU
ANYWHERE.
>> COME ON, HOJO, FORGET THAT
SILLY FAMILY TREE!
>> HUH?
OH, WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
>> BE QUIET.
IT'LL BE OVER QUICKLY.
>> ARE YOU THE ONES KILLING THE
MONKS AND THE SHRINE KEEPERS?
I HEARD THE DEMON WAS A FEMALE
WITH AN INFANT.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT
THIS INFANT.
IT COULD VERY WELL BE MORE EVIL
THAN THE WOMAN.
>> A PRIEST LIKE YOU SHOULD BE
ABLE TO SEE THE BORDER BETWEEN
THIS LIFE AND THE NEXT.
>> NEXT TIME, ENTEI, THE DEMON
HORSE UNLEASHED.
>> THAT'S JUST A STUPID HORSE.