>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU
WITH MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> KIKYO SHOWS UP AT THE BASE OF
THE SACRED MOUNT HAKUREI.
GINKOTSU RETURNS EVEN MORE
POWERFUL THAN BEFORE.
THEN SUIKOTSU, THE ONE WITH THE
SPLIT PERSONALITY,
FINALLY AWAKENS.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> GRR!
>> AAH!
OH!
>> DR. SUIKOTSU!
>> [BOTH SCREAMING AT ONCE]
HUH?
>> PLEASE!
NO!
>> UHH!
>> WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
>> ISN'T HE PART OF
THE BAND OF SEVEN?
>> DR. SUIKOTSU.
>> [GROANING] I'M ALL RIGHT.
ARE EITHER OF YOU HURT?
>> NO.
>> WE'RE OK.
>> AHH.
HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> NUH?
>> DR. SUIKOTSU?
>> HUH!
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
DR. SUIKOTSU?
>> GOOD. HE'S AWAKE.
>> YES.
>> HE IS.
>> AAH!
>> [LAUGHS]
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
JUST WHAT ARE YOU?
>> HA HA HA HA.
WHO, ME?
I'M SUIKOTSU OF THE
BAND OF SEVEN.
>> [GROANING]
>> DAMN YOU, SUIKOTSU.
>> [LAUGHS]
THAT RIDICULOUS DO-GOODER
PHYSICIAN.
HE'S HELD ME BACK FOR
FAR TOO LONG.
>> BUT HE...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HE'S AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT
PERSON THAN HE WAS BEFORE.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT SUIKOTSU.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF HE POSSESSES
TWO DIFFERENT HEARTS.
>> I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> HUH?
>> I'VE HEARD OF IT BEFORE.
IT'S CALLED A SPLIT PERSONALITY.
ANOTHER COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
PERSONALITY HIDDEN IN THE
SUBCONSCIOUS HAS EMERGED.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT ALL THAT
STUFF, BUT I DO KNOW THAT I WAS
RIGHT ABOUT YOU BELONGING TO THE
BAND OF SEVEN.
>> SUIKOTSU, HERE YOU GO.
>> [GRUNTING]
SO, THEN, I SEEM TO RECALL
YOU WERE ASKING TO DO BATTLE
WITH ME.
WELL, YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET
YOUR WISH.
>> [GROWLING]
>> HUH? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU TOO FRIGHTENED TO FIGHT
WITHOUT YOUR MIGHTY SWORD?
>> HA.
NOT LIKELY.
ARE THOSE CLAWS OF YOURS
ALL YOU GOT GOING FOR YOU?
CAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO NEED A
HECK OF A LOT MORE THAN THAT,
YOU FILTHY, TWO-FACED LIAR.
>> YOU BETTER SHOW MORE RESPECT
THAN THAT.
YAH!
>> YAH!
>> HUH?
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> UHH.
YOU'RE A QUICK ONE, AREN'T YOU?
>> HA.
I'LL CUT YOU INTO LITTLE PIECES.
HMPH.
>> [GROWLING]
>> DIE!
>> HUH!
YOUR MOVES ARE TOO SHOWY.
>> HUH?
>> I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT CLOSE
QUARTERS COMBAT IS ALL ABOUT!
>> UHH!
UHH! UHH!
UHH!
IF YOU KEEP BACKING AWAY LIKE
THIS, HOW WILL YOU EVER TURN ME
INTO MINCEMEAT?
>> YAH!
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
TOO MUCH FOR YOU?
>> WHY, YOU...
>> [GRUNTING]
>> WHAT?
>> [GROWLING]
YAH!
>> OHH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> YAHHH!
DAMN YOU, SUIKOTSU.
>> [GROWLING]
[SLURP]
NOW, DIE!
>> [BOTH GRUNTING]
>> AAH!
UHH!
HUH?
>> IT'S OVER.
>> STOP!
>> HUH?
>> DOCTOR, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU?
>> PLEASE GO BACK TO THE WAY
YOU ONCE WERE.
>> HUH?
UHH.
>> [GROANING]
GO AWAY.
[GRUNTING] GO AWAY.
>> WHAT THE HECK IS GOING ON?
>> WELL, THIS IS INCONVENIENT.
SUIKOTSU HASN'T COMPLETELY
AWAKENED YET.
WELL, THEN.
DO YOUR THING, GINKOTSU.
>> GRR.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> KIKYO!
>> [BOTH GRUNTING]
>> [GRUNTING]
KEEP YOUR EYE ON YOUR OPPONENT.
>> [GROWLING]
>> NO, KIKYO!
>> IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE INUYASHA
CAN GET TO HER!
>> THEN IT'S UP TO US.
>> AHH!
>> HEY, BE CAREFUL!
>> I'LL GO.
STAY HERE.
>> HANG ON, MIROKU.
I THOUGHT YOU COULDN'T USE YOUR
WIND TUNNEL YET.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I HAVE TO GO ANYWAY.
>> BUT, MIROKU.
>> SANGO, I WANT YOU TO STAY
CLOSE TO KAGOME, BUT CAN YOU
MAKE A PATH FOR ME
WITH YOUR WEAPON?
>> YOU KNOW I CAN.
HAH!
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
HUH.
>> NOT SO FAST.
YOU HAVEN'T GOT TIME TO RESCUE
HER RIGHT NOW.
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT ME INSTEAD.
>> [GROWLING]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [BOTH GRUNTING]
>> HUH.
IF YOU WANT HER LIFE TO BE
SPARED, YOU'LL HAVE TO DEFEAT
ME FIRST.
>> [ENGINE RUMBLING]
>> DAMN.
IF ONLY I HAD MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> KIKYO!
KIKYO!
>> LADY KIKYO!
[SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY]
>> [LAUGHS]
>> UHH.
>> [GROWLING]
>> THANK YOU, KIRARA.
HUH!
[GRUNTING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> UHH!
>> [GASPS]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> AAH!
>> OH, HE DID IT!
>> MIROKU!
>> [BOTH GRUNTING]
>> HUH.
KIKYO, I'M GLAD YOU'RE SAFE.
>> [GROWLING]
>> HA.
ACTUALLY, WE NEVER WERE
AFTER THE GIRL.
>> UHH.
>> OHH!
>> OH, BOY.
WHY DO I ALWAYS GET STUCK
WITH THE DIRTY WORK?
>> IF WE KILL THE CHILDREN,
THERE WILL BE NOTHING LEFT
TO DISTRACT SUIKOTSU.
THEN HE'LL BE ABLE TO SUPPRESS
THAT TROUBLESOME DOCTOR.
[LAUGHS]
>> [WHIMPERING]
HUH?
AAH!
>> DON'T WORRY.
IT'LL ALL BE OVER QUICK.
>> AAH!
>> STOP!
>> AWW.
>> [GRUNTING]
PLEASE STOP!
I BEG YOU!
UHH.
>> HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> [GRUMBLING] SUIKOTSU.
COME ON.
>> SOMETHING IS PREVENTING
SUIKOTSU FROM COMPLETELY
TAKING OVER.
IF WE KILL THE CHILDREN,
IT MAY PUSH HIM OVER THE EDGE
AND WE MAY LOSE HIM.
COULD IT BE THE BARRIER
OF MOUNT HAKUREI?
>> [GRUNTING]
THAT'S IT.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING DOWN.
[GRUNTING]
>> I HATE TO DISAPPOINT YOU,
BUT IT SEEMS WE CAN'T REMAIN
IN THIS PLACE ANY LONGER.
[GRUNTS]
THIS IS IT FOR TODAY.
COME, SUIKOTSU.
LET'S GO.
>> BUT WHY?
>> COME ON.
LET'S GO, SUIKOTSU.
>> [GRUMBLING] YOU BASTARDS!
>> [GRUNTING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
>> HE WON'T GET AWAY!
>> [GROWLING]
>> UHH!
[GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA!
BYE-BYE FOR NOW!
>> DAMN IT.
HOW IRRITATING.
>> [GROWLING]
>> LADY KIKYO!
PLEASE, WAKE UP, LADY KIKYO!
>> KIKYO.
HAVE THE SOULS OF THE DEAD
ALL LEFT HER BODY?
>> INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> KIKYO'S SOUL COLLECTORS.
HUH?
>> THEY'RE DISAPPEARING?
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
>> THEY CAN'T GET ANY CLOSER.
MOVE HER AWAY.
>> HUH?
>> WE HAVE TO MOVE KIKYO
WELL AWAY FROM THIS PLACE.
OTHERWISE, SHE WON'T BE
ABLE TO WAKE UP.
I THINK.
>> KAGOME.
>> SO, WHAT SHALL WE DO?
>> HUH?
>> WOULD YOU PREFER THAT I BE
THE ONE TO CARRY HER?
>> INUYASHA SHOULD BE THE ONE
TO DO IT.
>> IS IT JUST ME OR ARE THINGS
A BIT TENSE HERE?
>> NO, SHIPPO.
IT ISN'T JUST YOU.
>> [EXHALES]
>> HUH?
HMM.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE THE TWO OF
THEM LIKE THIS, BUT I GUESS IT
CAN'T BE HELPED.
>> MIROKU, DOES INUYASHA
STILL HAVE FEELINGS FOR KIKYO?
>> ONE REALLY CAN'T HELP HAVING
THE GREATEST ADMIRATION FOR
KAGOME'S GENEROSITY.
>> UH...
>> HMM?
>> IF IT'S NOT TOO MUCH TO ASK,
COULD YOU CHANGE THE SUBJECT?
>> SURE. OK.
>> WE'RE, UH, VERY SORRY.
>> AND VERY SCARED.
>> HUH?
WAS IT SOMETHING I SAID?
KIKYO.
>> INUYASHA.
>> HMM.
>> WHERE AM I?
>> AWAY FROM THE VILLAGE.
>> I SEE.
SO, THEN, I TAKE IT MY
SOUL COLLECTORS WERE NOT ABLE
TO APPROACH THE VILLAGE.
>> NO.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
TO THEM?
>> THE BAND OF SEVEN?
>> THOSE CURSED MEN WHO POSSESS
THE DEFILED SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> THEY'VE RETREATED,
BUT THEY TOOK SUIKOTSU
WITH THEM.
>> I SEE.
KAGOME?
>> YES?
>> YOU MUST HAVE SEEN IT.
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
IN SUIKOTSU'S NECK.
>> I DID.
I SAW THE PURE JEWEL SHARD
BECOME CLOUDY.
>> AND THEN HE WENT AWAY,
DIDN'T HE?
IT'S THIS PLACE.
IT'S BECAUSE OF THE LAND.
>> KIKYO, WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO SAY?
>> THIS LAND IS WICKED.
IT DOES NOT ALLOW ANYONE
WITH A DEMONIC AURA TO APPROACH.
IT IS BECAUSE MOUNT HAKUREI
IS PURIFYING THE AIR
OF THE AREAS THAT SURROUND IT.
>> MOUNT HAKUREI.
I'VE HEARD OF IT BEFORE.
IT IS A SACRED MOUNTAIN
WHICH ABSOLVES AND CLEANSES
CRIMINALS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE MAN KNOWN AS DR. SUIKOTSU
WAS ABLE TO LIVE HERE BECAUSE,
DEEP DOWN INSIDE, HE HAD A PURE,
UNTAINTED HEART.
>> BUT HIS OTHER PERSONALITY,
THE SUIKOTSU WHO BELONGED TO THE
BAND OF SEVEN, FINALLY SURFACED,
SO HE WASN'T ABLE TO STAY HERE.
>> SO, THEN, THE REASON THEY
STOPPED FIGHTING AND RETREATED
WAS THEY WERE TOO CLOSE TO
MOUNT HAKUREI?
>> PURE HAS BECOME IMPURE.
IMPURE HAS BECOME PURE.
GOOD IS EVIL.
EVIL IS GOOD.
TO LIVE IS TO DIE.
TO DIE IS TO LIVE.
YES, MOUNT HAKUREI IS INDEED
TOO PURE.
>> HMM.
MOUNT HAKUREI, HUH?
>> SO, MIROKU, WHAT SHOULD
WE DO?
>> LET'S GO CHECK IT OUT.
I'M CURIOUS.
>> KIKYO, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> HUH.
>> HUH?
>> LADY KIKYO.
>> I CHOOSE TO STAY HERE.
I WANT TO STAY CLOSE
TO THOSE CHILDREN FOR A WHILE.
BESIDES...
>> YES?
>> EVEN IF I WISH TO,
I CANNOT GO.
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA, YOU SAW THEM.
YOU SAW MY SOUL COLLECTORS
BEING REPELLED BY THE AURA
OF THIS LAND.
>> HMM.
>> IT TOOK EVERYTHING I HAD
JUST TO STAND AT THE BASE OF
THE MOUNTAIN.
>> KIKYO.
>> HMM.
INUYASHA, DO YOU STILL...
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
HEY, MIROKU.
WHY DO YOU THING KAGOME
IS RIDING WITH SANGO?
>> PROBABLY BECAUSE SHE DOESN'T
WANT TO BE CARRIED BY YOU.
>> BUT WHAT THE HECK DID I DO?
>> WHAT YOU DID OR DIDN'T DO
DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
AT THIS POINT.
KAGOME FEELS EMOTIONALLY
BETRAYED.
WOMEN ARE VERY SENSITIVE.
KAGOME IS HURT BECAUSE
SHE THINKS THAT YOU MAY STILL
HAVE FEELINGS FOR KIKYO.
YOU SHOULD LEAVE HER ALONE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
IT WOULD NOT BE PARTICULARLY
WISE TO PROVOKE HER
UNNECESSARILY RIGHT NOW.
>> HUH?
>> HEY, KAGOME!
>> INUYASHA!
>> IDIOT.
>> COME ON, ANSWER ME ALREADY.
WHY THE HECK ARE YOU
IGNORING ME?
HEY, KAGOME!
>> NOT NOW.
>> [GULPS] AAH!
>> HUH?
>> IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY,
THEN LET'S HEAR IT, OK?
>> DON'T BOTHER.
>> COME ON.
I KNOW YOU'RE ANGRY.
>> NO, I'M NOT ANGRY.
>> GRR.
ANYWAY, THIS IS NO TIME
FOR US TO ARGUE.
YOU REALIZE THAT, DON'T YOU?
HMPH.
GRR.
UH...
>> INUYASHA?
>> YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
>> WE'VE TALKED ABOUT IT BEFORE,
HAVEN'T WE?
ABOUT ME STAYING WITH YOU.
>> UH...
>> I KNOW THAT THERE'S A BOND
BETWEEN YOU AND KIKYO,
AND I KNOW I CAN'T EVER ASK YOU
TO FORGET ABOUT HER.
AND YET...
I'M GOING TO STAND BY YOU,
INUYASHA.
IT'S WHAT I KNOW I HAVE TO DO.
>> HMM.
KAGOME.
>> SO, I'M NOT GOING TO WORRY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
>> UH...
>> THERE'S ONE THING, THOUGH.
>> HMM?
>> WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO PICK
A FIGHT WITH ME?
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST
LEAVE ME ALONE?
>> UHH!
>> THIS IS ALREADY HARD ENOUGH!
>> AAH!
>> HEY, WAIT.
I WAS RIGHT.
YOU ARE ANGRY AFTER ALL.
>> SIT, BOY!
>> AAH!
>> SIT, BOY, SIT, BOY, SIT, BOY!
SIT, BOY, SIT, BOY, SIT, BOY!
SIT, SIT, SIT, SIT, SIT!
SIT, BOY!
>> I TOLD HIM NOT TO PROVOKE
HER UNNECESSARILY.
>> OH, MAN.
THAT HAS REALLY GOT TO HURT.
>> STOP!
>> SO, TELL ME, RENKOTSU.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
>> HMM?
HEY, ISN'T THAT KOHAKU?
>> HE'S COME TO MEET US.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
LET'S GO MEET UP WITH
BIG BROTHER.
THEN THE BAND OF SEVEN
WILL BE AT FULL FORCE AGAIN.
>> SO, THAT'S IT, IS IT?
FINALLY FOUND IT.
[LAUGHS]
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> THE STRONGEST OF THE BAND OF
SEVEN, BANKOTSU, BEGINS AN
ASSAULT ON A CASTLE TO REGAIN
HIS GIANT HALBEARD.
[INDISTINCT]
>> THOSE BASTARDS IN THAT CASTLE
BEHEADED US.
HMPH.
I FEEL STRONGER THAN I DID
BEFORE I DIED.
>> WHAT?
DON'T TELL ME THEY'RE ALSO
AFTER KOGA'S SHIKON
JEWEL SHARDS.
NEXT ON "INUYASHA," ENTER
BANKOTSU, THE LEADER OF THE
BAND OF SEVEN.
>> PREPARE TO MEET MY VENGEANCE.