>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS BETWEEN
US.
>> A NEW HOPE.
A BRIGHT FUTURE BEGINS NOW.
>> OUR JOURNEY BEGAN WITH THE
SHATTERING OF THE SACRED JEWEL,
AND NOW THE SHARDS GIVE INUYASHA
THE POWER TO PUT AN END TO IT
ALL.
WILL WE LIVE OR DIE?
THIS IS THE FINAL BATTLE.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
INUYASHA.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> [ROARING]
>> THE DEMON MOUNTAIN WAS
KILLED?
>> YES.
>> [ROARING]
>> [GASPING]
>> IT WAS, UH, 3 DAYS AGO.
SOMETHING THAT LOOKED LIKE
SHAFTS OF LIGHT STRUCK THE DEMON
MOUNTAIN.
>> [GROANING]
>> ARE YOU CERTAIN HE DIED?
>> HE FELL AND LAY THERE
MOTIONLESS, BUT EVERYONE'S TOO
AFRAID TO GET ANYWHERE NEAR IT.
>> A DEMON MOUNTAIN.
THE ONLY ONE I CAN THINK THEY
MEANT IS GAKUSANJIN.
THE STRANGE THING IS DON'T SENSE
ANY DEMONIC AURA AROUND HERE.
>> MM-HMM.
IT'S JUST AN ORDINARY MOUNTAIN.
>> HMM?
NO.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> HUH?
>> HAVEN'T HAD ENOUGH?
>> TAKE SOME...
CRYSTALS OF MY DEMONIC AURA.
GRAB A FEW.
WHEN YOU ARE NEAR THE FUYOUHEKI,
THE AURA OF THE CRYSTALS WILL
DISAPPEAR.
IF YOU MOVE AWAY FROM IT, THE
AURA WILL REAPPEAR.
>> THIS WILL HELP IN LOCATING
NARAKU.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE GAKUSANJIN HAS
DECIDED TO TRUST US.
>> YES.
>> THANKS.
THAT WILL HELP.
>> ENOUGH.
NOW GO.
>> GAKUSANJIN.
>> HE MUST HAVE PURSUED NARAKU
EVEN AFTER WE PARTED WAYS WITH
HIM.
NARAKU PROBABLY DESTROYED HIM.
>> THEN, YOU THINK NARAKU DID
THIS?
>> THIS IS A HUMAN SCENT.
>> HUMAN?
>> IT SMELLS LIKE A FEW HUMANS.
THE SCENT'S STILL FRESH.
SO, THAT MEANS SOME HUMANS MUST
HAVE COME HERE AFTER GAKUSANJIN
DIED FOR WHATEVER REASON.
>> WHY, DO YOU THINK?
>> THE LOCAL PEOPLE SAID THEY
DON'T APPROACH THIS AREA BECAUSE
THEY'RE AFRAID OF GAKUSANJIN.
>> THERE IT IS!
>> PLEASE, AESTHETICS!
WE NEED YOUR HELP HERE!
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YOUNG MAN, HOW CAN WE EVER
REPAY YOU?
>> JUST GIVE US A CART AND WE'LL
CALL IT EVEN.
>> A CART, YOU SAY?
WHAT DO YOU WANT THAT FOR?
>> WE WILL USE IT TO DISPOSE OF
THE DEMON'S REMAINS.
>> THOSE AESTHETICS WERE STILL
CHILDREN.
ODD, DON'T YOU THINK?
>> OH, THEY'RE PRETTY INCREDIBLE
LITTLE FELLAS.
>> MASTER GORYOMARU, WE
DESTROYED THE DEMON.
>> GOOD WORK.
YOU MAY GO AND REST.
I WILL PRAY FOR ITS REPOSE.
>> WHAT?
AESTHETICS ARE GOING AROUND
SLAYING DEMONS?
>> YES.
A GROUP OF AESTHETICS WHO LIVE
IN A SACRED MOUNTAIN IN THE
EAST.
EACH ONE OF THEM CARRIES A
STRANGE WEAPON THAT LOOKS LIKE A
GREAT URN.
>> AND THE LADS DESTROY DEMONS
WITH THE LIGHT THAT COMES OUT OF
THOSE URNS.
>> HMM.
>> YOU SAID EACH ONE OF THEM.
HOW MANY AESTHETICS ARE THERE IN
ALL?
WOULD YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE ANY
IDEA OF THEIR NUMBER?
>> IT WAS 3 OF THEM THAT CAME
THE OTHER DAY.
>> AND THERE WERE RUMORS THAT
THERE WERE SEVERAL MORE THOUGH,
RIGHT?
>> WELL, WE KNOW FOR SURE IT WAS
STRANGE SHAFTS OF LIGHT THAT
BROUGHT GAKUSANJIN DOWN.
>> YEAH.
IT'S GOTTA BE THE SAME GUYS
THAT DID IT.
LET'S GO.
>> HMM?!
HMM.
YOU SEE THAT?
SOME OF THOSE PEOPLE LOOKED LIKE
DEMONS.
>> PERHAPS WE SHOULD NOTIFY THE
AESTHETICS THERE ARE MORE DEMONS
ABOUT.
>> SO, THAT'S THE SACRED
MOUNTAIN OF THE EAST.
>> WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
>> OH, JEEZ.
THIS WAS MY FAVORITE PAIR OF
SHOES.
>> HA!
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN WALKED THAT
MUCH AND THEY'RE BROKEN.
>> JUST HANG IN THERE A LITTLE
BIT LONGER, GUYS.
>> SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK,
INUYASHA?
THINK THERE'S ANY CHANCE THESE
AESTHETICS ARE SOMEHOW CONNECTED
TO NARAKU?
>> PROBABLY.
ESPECIALLY SINCE THEY DEFEATED
GAKUSANJIN.
THAT SCENT!
WATCH OUT, KAGOME!
>> AAGH!
>> SHAFTS OF LIGHT!
>> HMM?!
IT'S COMING FROM OVER THAT WAY!
>> DARN IT!
WE DIDN'T HIT HIM!
>> IT'S NOT OUR FAULT.
THE TARGET'S SMALLER THAN USUAL.
>> WHAT?!
THEY'RE THE AESTHETICS?
>> THEY'RE STILL JUST YOUNG
CHILDREN.
>> [GROWLS]
NO MISTAKE.
THIS IS THE SAME SCENT THAT WAS
LEFT BEFORE GAKUSANJIN.
>> THOSE...
CHILDREN KILLED HIM?
>> HEY, HUMANS ARE WITH HIM,
TOO!
>> WOMAN, YOU BETTER GET AWAY
FROM THAT DEMON--UNLESS YOU WANT
TO DIE.
>> WHAT ON EARTH ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?!
>> STAY BACK, KAGOME!
WHAT ARE YOU HUMAN BRATS DOING
WITH SUCH DANGEROUS WEAPONS?!
WHO GAVE THEM TO YOU?!
>> HA!
WHY?
WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
>> ESPECIALLY 'CAUSE YOU'RE
ABOUT TO BE SLAIN.
>> SHUT UP, YOU BRATS!
YOU'LL ANSWER ME ONE WAY OR
ANOTHER!
>> PERISH, VILE DEMON!
>> MOVE, INUYASHA!
>> YOU'LL BE PIERCED BY THE
LIGHT!
>> HUH?!
THESE SHAFTS OF LIGHT HAVE
SUBSTANCE.
[GRUNTS]
>> HUH?!
>> YOU SEE THAT?
>> THEY'RE DEMONS.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING?!
>> HOW DARE YOU DO THAT TO THE
LIGHT OF THE GORYO URNS?!
>> HOW DID YOU GET THOSE URNS?!
WHERE DID THEY COME FROM?!
>> SILENCE, DEMON!
>> WE'RE TAKING YOU WITH US TO
OUR GRAVES.
>> FINE WITH ME.
AND YOU CAN DIE HERE IF YOU
WANT.
>> COME ON, INUYASHA.
LISTEN:
YOU KIDS SHOULDN'T HAVE THOSE
URNS.
IF YOU KEEP GOING AROUND DOING
DANGEROUS THINGS LIKE THAT,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY GONNA GET HURT
ONE DAY.
>> LEAVE US ALONE!
>> DEMONS WILL NEVER DEFEAT US
IF WE HAVE THE GORYO URNS!
>> ONE JUST DID, IN CASE YOU
HADN'T NOTICED.
>> SHUT UP!
>> YOU'LL REGRET THIS!
>> THE NEXT TIME WE MEET,
YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS!
>> COME BACK HERE, YOU BRATS!
>> LET THEM GO FOR NOW,
INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> WE CAN FOLLOW THEM AT OUR OWN
PACE.
>> HMM.
>> [GRUNTS]
ARE YOU OK?!
>> IT'S OUTRAGEOUS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SOMEBODY
ACTUALLY TRAINED THOSE KIDS IN
THE ART OF DEMON-SLAYING.
>> AT FIRST, I THOUGHT THEY
MIGHT BE NARAKU'S HENCHMEN,
BUT ON SECOND THOUGHT, THEY SEEM
FAR TOO INEXPERIENCED.
>> MAYBE.
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE SOMEONE'S
PULLING THE STRINGS BEHIND THOSE
LITTLE KIDS.
AND WHOEVER THAT IS MUST BE
CONNECTED TO NARAKU.
[BIRDS CAWING]
>> SO, IT'S TRUE THAT GAKUSANJIN
DIED.
NARAKU PASSED THE FUYOUHEKI TO
THE INFANT.
AND IF GAKUSANJIN PURSUED THEM
AND WAS KILLED, THEN THERE MUST
BE SOME LEADS TO THE INFANT
AROUND HERE.
>> INUYASHA?
>> YEAH.
>> [GASPS]
THERE'S SOMETHING CREEPY ABOUT
THAT TEMPLE.
>> THIS DEMONIC AURA IS STRONG.
>> HERE IT COMES!
>> SHAFTS OF LIGHT.
>> IF I CUT AWAY THEIR INSIDES,
THERE WON'T BE A PROBLEM.
[GRUNTS]
WIND SCAR!
>> [GASPS]
>> THE URN DOESN'T WORK ON THEM.
>> THEY'RE ALL JUST LITTLE KIDS.
>> AND WE'RE GOING AFTER THEM.
>> [SCREAMS]
>> MASTER GORYOMARU!
PLEASE HELP US, MASTER
GORYOMARU.
>> YOU IDIOT!
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE PROTECTING
MASTER GORYOMARU.
>> STEP BACK,
ALL OF YOU.
>> HUH?
[GROWLS]
>> A DEMON, IS IT?
YOU HAVE THE AUDACITY TO APPEAR
BEFORE ME?
>> [GASPS]
IS HE A DEMON?
>> THIS GUY'S BODY REEKS WITH
THE SMELL OF DEMONS.
HE'S GOTTA BE ONE OF NARAKU'S
MINIONS.
>> ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
>> HMM.
NOW THINGS SHOULD GET
INTERESTING.
>> [GROWLING]
>> HMM?
DEMONS FROM AROUND HERE.
WHERE ARE THEY GOING?
>> HUH?
>> HUH?!
>> [SCREAMS]
>> THERE ARE SO MANY OF THEM!
>> CHILDREN, PICK UP YOUR
GORYO URNS.
>> WE--WE CAN'T USE THEM!
THEIR INNER LIGHT WAS CUT UP!
>> THAT EXPLAINS IT.
THE DEMONS THOUGHT THEY COULD
DESTROY THE TEMPLE NOW THAT THE
GORYO URNS ARE USELESS.
>> HA!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA INTERFERE!
HUH?
[GRUNTS]
>> THE SAME LIGHT AS
THE GORYO URNS THE CHILDREN USE!
>> WHERE'S THAT LIGHT COMING
FROM?
>> THEY'RE STILL HERE.
>> THERE ARE TOO MANY OF THEM.
>> HA!
WIND SCAR!
>> [ROARING]
>> HIRAKOTE!
HYAH!
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> INCREDIBLE!
YOU SEE THAT?!
>> INUYASHA AND HIS FRIENDS ARE
HERE, TOO?
>> DESPICABLE.
>> HUH?
>> YOU'RE A DEMON,
SO WHY DO YOU KILL OTHER DEMONS?
>> HA!
THAT'S WHAT I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU!
>> YOU THERE, GORYOMARU,
ARE YOU NOT ALSO A DEMON?
>> HOW DARE YOU!
MASTER GORYOMARU IS A HUMAN!
>> HE IS NOT A DEMON!
>> HE'S AN IMPORTANT AESTHETIC.
>> IT IS TRUE.
THIS ARM IS FROM A DEMON.
HOWEVER, AS YOU CAN PLAINLY SEE,
IT MOVES AS I WILL IT TO.
I OVERCAME THE DEMON WHO
POSSESSED ME AND TRIED TO DEVOUR
ME AND MY SPIRITUAL POWERS.
MY REAL ARM WAS INDEED EATEN,
BUT THIS ARM WORKS WELL TO
DESTROY THE VILE DEMONS.
>> DESTROY THE VILE DEMONS?
>> BOY, THAT IS ONE HARSH
DEMON-HATER.
>> AND YOU GIVE KIDS STRANGE
URNS TO SLAY DEMONS FOR YOU?
HOW ARE YOU GONNA EXPLAIN THAT
ONE?!
>> HUH?!
>> I BET YOUR THE ONE THAT
ORDERED THEM TO KILL GAKUSANJIN,
TOO!
>> GAKUSANJIN?
>> THE DEMON OF THE MOUNTAIN,
THE DEMON WHO PREFERRED TO STAY
DORMANT AS A MOUNTAIN RATHER
THAN FIGHT USELESS BATTLES.
GAKUSANJIN WAS AFTER ANOTHER
DEMON--OR RATHER A HALF-DEMON
WHO HAD DISTURBED HIS SLEEP.
AND THE NAME OF THE HALF-DEMON
HE SPOKE OF IS NARAKU.
>> NARAKU?
>> I WANT TO KNOW THE REASON YOU
KILLED THE INNOCENT GAKUSANJIN.
>> CHILDREN, IS THIS TRUE?
>> WELL, YOU SEE...
>> WE CAN'T REALLY TELL IF THE
DEMONS ARE GOOD OR BAD.
>> DOES THAT MEAN IT WAS JUST A
COINCIDENCE THAT THEY KILLED
GAKUSANJIN?
THAT THEY'RE NOT CONNECTED TO
NARAKU?
>> I'D LIKE TO TELL YOU TO LEAVE
AT ONCE SEEING AS YOUR BUSINESS
HERE IS DONE.
BUT IF YOU LEAVE NOW, YOU'LL
SURELY BE ATTACKED BY DEMONS IN
THE AREA.
I WILL ALLOW YOU TO SPEND THE
NIGHT IN THE TEMPLE.
>> HEY, I AIN'T FINISHED TALKING
TO YOU!
>> INUYASHA, LET'S ACCEPT HIS
HOSPITALITY.
>> HUH?
>> STRANGE THAT HE DIDN'T KICK
US OUT.
>> SO, HE'S A GOOD GUY?
>> WELL...
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT HIS
STORY?
>> WHEN WE MENTIONED GAKUSANJIN
AND NARAKU'S NAMES, HIS FACE
DIDN'T SHOW ANY SIGN OF
RECOGNITION.
>> HA.
THIS IS SOMEONE CAPABLE OF
PUTTING ON QUITE THE CHARADE.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT WOULDN'T
MAKE 'EM FLINCH.
>> I WONDER IF NARAKU IS NEARBY.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
>> I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
BUT AS LONG AS NARAKU HAS THE
FUYOUHEKI, WE WON'T BE ABLE TO
FIND HIM.
>> TOO BAD WE DON'T HAVE THE
CRYSTAL FRAGMENTS FROM
GAKUSANJIN.
>> HEY.
>> HMM?
>> IT'S TIME FOR DINNER.
>> HMM.
[GROWLS]
>> [MUNCHING]
>> GORYOMARU IS INVOLVED WITH
NARAKU, I'M SURE OF IT.
BUT WHAT IS HE PLANNING TO DO BY
USING THESE KIDS?
HEY!
HOW COME GORYOMARU ISN'T EATING
WITH US?
>> 'CAUSE HE'S BUSY PUTTING
LIGHT INTO THE GORYO URNS.
>> HMM?
>> HE SAYS IT MAKES HIM VERY
EXHAUSTED.
>> HMM.
>> WHY DO YOU KIDS DO SOMETHING
SO DANGEROUS?
WHERE ARE YOUR PARENTS ANYWAY?
>> AIN'T GOT ANY.
>> OUR PARENTS ARE ALL DEAD.
THEY WERE EATEN BY DEMONS.
>> ALL OF YOU HERE ARE ORPHANS?
>> YEAH, AND IF THE MASTER
DIDN'T TAKE US IN, WE'D HAVE
DIED ON THE ROADSIDE.
>> THAT'S WHY WE'RE HELPING
MASTER GORYOMARU WITH HIS WORK
HERE AT THE TEMPLE.
>> OUR WORST ENEMIES ARE THOSE
DEMONS.
>> OH.
>> WHAT A CREEPY TEMPLE.
THE DEMONS ARE COMING IN HORDES,
LIKE THEY'RE BEING DRAWN HERE.
STRANGE THAT THEY DON'T GO
INSIDE...
ESPECIALLY WHEN THERE'S NO
BARRIER.
THERE'S SOMETHING GOING ON...
AND I HAVE TO FIND OUT WHAT IT
IS.
YOU DEMONS, YOU ARE GOING TO
BECOME MY SOLDIERS!
>> [ROARING]
>> HMM?
>> DEMONS ARE ATTACKING THE
TEMPLE!
>> WHAT WILL WE DO?!
THE URNS AREN'T READY!
>> YOU GUYS JUST STAY PUT INSIDE
THE TEMPLE!
>> [GROANING]
>> HIRAKOTE!
>> THESE DEMONS ARE ALREADY
DEAD.
>> MOVE!
WIND SCAR!
>> IT'S NO GOOD!
THEY'RE STILL COMING!
>> DAMN!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO KILL DEAD
DEMONS?!
>> LOOKS LIKE A JOB FOR ME!
WIND TUNNEL!
SAIMYOUSHO!
>> MIROKU, COVER YOUR WIND
TUNNEL!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> WHAT ARE SAIMYOUSHO DOING
HERE?
>> HMM.
I'LL FIND OUT IF THE INFANT IS
IN THIS TEMPLE.
SOMETHING TELLS ME HE IS.
>> NOW I'VE GOT IT.
THIS IS KAGURA'S DANCE OF THE
DEAD!
>> INUYASHA!
>> I'VE GOTTA TAKE OUT KAGURA,
OTHERWISE THIS WON'T END.
HUH?
IF KAGURA IS ATTACKING, DOES IT
MEAN GORYOMARU ISN'T ONE OF
NARAKU'S HENCHMEN?
>> [ROARING]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> FOX FIRE!
>> YOU BOYS, YOU SHOULDN'T BE
OUT HERE!
>> WE'LL BE OK--AS LONG AS WE
HAVE OUR GORYO URNS.
>> MASTER GORYOMARU!
>> MY BOYS!
>> WE'LL USE THE GORYO URNS!
>> DON'T WORRY, MASTER,
WE CAN HANDLE THIS.
>> DIE!
>> HUH?!
>> THE GORYO URNS DON'T WORK ON
THESE DEMONS.
>> HUH?
>> YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS!
>> MASTER GORYOMARU?
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> HE CAN'T MOVE.
HE'S ALWAYS LIKE THIS AFTER HE
REFILLS THE URNS WITH LIGHT.
>> [GASPS]
>> [GROANS]
>> HE'S SO PALE.
>> COME ON OUT, KAGURA.
I KNOW YOU'RE AROUND HERE!
>> HA.
SO, WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WHAT'S YOUR CONNECTION TO THIS
TEMPLE, INUYASHA?
>> HOW COME YOU'RE ATTACKING
THIS TEMPLE?
DOES THAT MEAN GORYOMARU IS
NARAKU'S ENEMY?
>> GORYOMARU?
DOES HE MEAN THE MAN IN THE
TEMPLE?
IT'S ALL STARTING TO COME
TOGETHER.
>> ANSWER ME, KAGURA!
>> YOU'RE IN MY WAY,
SO MOVE IT!
>> [GRUNTS]
>> [GROWLING]
>> YOU WITCH!
COME BACK HERE!
>> EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HMM?
>> HMM?!
>> MASTER GORYOMARU!
>> MY POWER IS RETURNING.
>> LOOK AT THAT, KAGOME!
>> I KNOW!
THE DEMON ARM IS REACTING TO THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> HUH?
>> HMM?
>> SUCH EYESORES.
>> KAGURA!
>> WHAT IS IT!
>> EVERYONE GET BACK!
>> DO NOT MOVE.
>> GORYOMARU!