- WHY WAS I DEFEATED?
- AAH!
- VICTORY IS MINE!
[GROWLING]
- OH, NO!
AAH!
DID I MAKE A MISTAKE SOMEWHERE?
NO. I'VE MADE NO ERRORS.
AS LONG AS I HAVE THIS SACRED
JEWEL, I CAN START OVER.
- WHO'S THERE?
- HMM?
- HOW DARE YOU TRESPASS HERE?
- IF YOU ARE HUMAN, BEGONE,
AND IF YOU ARE A DEMON,
WE WILL SLAY YOU!
- STAND DOWN!
I AM PRIESTESS TSUBAKI.
I TRAINED AT THIS SHRINE.
- OH, HOW NOSTALGIC.
NOT MUCH HAS CHANGED
SINCE I WAS LAST HERE.
- MY NAME IS MOMIJI.
- AND MY NAME IS BOTAN.
- ONLY YOU TWO PROTECT
THE SHRINE NOW?
- YES. YOU SEE,
THE TWO OF US WERE THE LAST
OF OUR MASTER'S DISCIPLES.
- I SEE.
- EXCUSE ME, PRIESTESS TSUBAKI.
WERE YOU ONCE ONE OF
THE MASTER'S DISCIPLES, AS WELL?
PARDON MY RUDENESS, BUT WOULD
YOU MIND IF I ASK YOUR AGE?
- YES, IT'S TRUE.
YOU LOOK VERY YOUNG.
- I AM MUCH OLDER THAN
BOTH OF YOU, OF COURSE.
MY YOUTHFULNESS IS
DUE TO MY TRAINING.
- IS THERE A SKILL
TO KEEP ONE YOUNG?
- OF SORTS. AND YOU, TOO,
MIGHT REAP SUCH BENEFITS
IF YOU CONTINUE YOUR TRAINING.
- HUH?
- HMM. IT'S NOT
VERY EASY, THOUGH.
- PRIESTESS TSUBAKI, WHY DID YOU
RETURN TO THIS SHRINE?
- IT'S BECAUSE I AM
BEING HUNTED BY A DEMON.
[GASP]
- A DEMON?
- WHAT SHALL I DO
WITH THESE TWO?
SHOULD I KILL THEM HERE AND NOW?
- WE WILL ASSIST YOU,
PRIESTESS TSUBAKI,
BECAUSE YOU ARE
OUR SISTER DISCIPLE.
- OH?
- I REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED NOW.
I WAS PLACED UNDER A CURSE
BY THE DARK PRIESTESS TSUBAKI.
- HEY.
[GASP]
ARE YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
- YES. I'M OK NOW.
- KAGOME!
- YOU'RE AWAKE, KAGOME.
- FEELING BETTER?
- KAGOME!
- LOOK, I'M ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
I'M JUST FINE!
- WAS THE DARK PRIESTESS WHO
PLACED THE CURSE NAMED TSUBAKI?
50 YEARS AGO, THERE WAS
A PRIESTESS BY THAT NAME
WHO WAS EQUAL
IN STATUS TO KIKYO.
- WHY DID SHE TURN INTO
AN EVIL PRIESTESS?
- THAT I DO NOT KNOW.
PERHAPS SHE MERELY SHARES
THE SAME NAME WITH ONE.
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I SENSE THE PRESENCE
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
- ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THAT, KAGOME?
- YES. I CAN FEEL IT CLEARLY.
- IT'S A HUGE SHARD,
THAT'S WHY.
- WHICH WAY IS IT?
- IT'S THAT WAY.
- WE'LL HAVE TO GO AFTER IT.
- CORRECT. WE MUSTN'T
PASS UP THIS CHANCE
TO GET A SACRED
JEWEL SHARD BACK.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, KAEDE?
DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE COMING WITH US!
- SHE IS A DARK PRIESTESS,
AFTER ALL,
SO I THOUGHT I, AS A PRIESTESS,
SHOULD ACCOMPANY YOU.
- DOESN'T "PRIESTESS"
BRING SOMEONE YOUNG TO MIND?
- KAGOME.
- INUYASHA--SIT, BOY!
- UNH!
- SUCH AN IMPUDENT FELLOW.
ONWARD WE GO!
- KIRARA!
- COME ON, INUYASHA.
- UNH! WHY, YOU...
[GIGGLES]
- THAT WAY.
- UNH!
- HUH? HEY, WAIT UP!
DON'T FORGET ABOUT ME!
- YOU LEARN QUICKLY, TSUBAKI.
- DO YOU MEAN THAT, MASTER?
- YES.
[LAUGHS]
- HMM. 60 YEARS HAVE PASSED.
IT'S NO SURPRISE THAT
MY MASTER HAS DIED.
- PRIESTESS TSUBAKI.
- HMM?
SPECIAL CHARMS THAT ARE
UNIQUE TO THIS SHRINE
KEEP ANY DEMONS FROM ENTERING.
WHERE COULD THEY BE LOCATED?
- LET US TAKE CARE OF THE DEMON,
PRIESTESS TSUBAKI.
- EVEN IF WE CANNOT SLAY IT,
WE CAN AT LEAST SLOW IT DOWN.
- ARE YOU CERTAIN?
THE ENEMY IS A TERRIBLE
EVIL DEMON.
- BUT WE HAVE TRAINED
HARD AND LONG, AS WELL.
- AND THEREFORE IT IS OUR DUTY
TO FIGHT EVIL DEMONS.
- THEN YOU MUST KEEP
THE DEMONS AT BAY
FOR AS LONG AS
YOU BOTH ARE ABLE.
- OF COURSE!
- DO YOU THINK THESE ARE GOING
TO BE ENOUGH, MOMIJI?
- I THINK ALL OF THESE
WILL WORK JUST FINE, BOTAN.
- IT'S OUR VERY
FIRST TIME, THOUGH.
- AND THAT'S ALL THE MORE
REASON FOR DOING IT.
- YOU'RE RIGHT. IT'S ALL PART OF
TRAINING AND EXPERIENCE.
- ONWARD!
- TO SLAY THE DEMON!
- YOU MUST NEVER
OPEN THESE DOORS.
THIS IS THE FORBIDDEN
TOWER OF MANY TREASURES.
- AHH!
FORBIDDEN, IS IT?
[WIND BLOWS]
IT'S YOU!
- NARAKU SENT ME TO GET
THE SACRED JEWEL BACK.
- THIS JEWEL BELONGS TO ME!
- I COULD BE WRONG, BUT DIDN'T
HE PROMISE TO GIVE IT TO YOU
IF YOU FULFILLED HIS WISH?
- I WILL FULFILL HIS WISH.
I'LL KILL BOTH
KAGOME AND INUYASHA.
BUT TO DO SO, I REQUIRE
THE SACRED JEWEL.
- HOW WILL YOU KILL THEM?
THEY DEFEATED YOU ONCE ALREADY.
- A GREAT POWER LIES WITHIN...
POWER THAT I PLAN TO USE
WITH THIS SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
- IT DOESN'T SOUND
VERY HOPEFUL TO ME AT ALL.
SHALL I TELL YOU
SOMETHING INTERESTING?
- WHAT IS IT?
- DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE ULTIMATE WAY TO USE
THE SACRED JEWEL?
[GASP]
- OVER THERE.
- I GOTCHA.
[SNARLING]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, KIRARA?
- DOWN THERE.
- HUH? WHAT IS THAT THING?
- A BARRIER.
WE PRIESTESSES PUT UP
SUCH PAPER TALISMANS
TO PREVENT DEMONS FROM ENTERING.
- DO YOU THINK THIS
IS TSUBAKI'S DOING?
- I SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL
BEYOND THIS BARRIER.
- DAMN. I'M GONNA TEAR
THIS STUPID BARRIER APART!
AAH!
OW! WHAT IS THIS?
- UH...UH...
WHOA!
- THIS IS NO TIME
FOR HORSING AROUND.
- HUH?
- THIS IS OBVIOUSLY A BARRIER
TO WARD AWAY DEMONS.
YOU SHOULD ALL STAND
BACK AND LET KAEDE
AND I DISMANTLE IT.
- MM-HMM.
- YOU'VE ARRIVED, DEMON!
WE'VE BEEN WAITING!
ARE YOU INUYASHA, THE DEMON
WHO SEEKS TO DESTROY
PRIESTESS TSUBAKI?
- WHAT? YOU'RE BOTH
ON TSUBAKI'S SIDE?
- PRIESTESS TSUBAKI
IS A SISTER DISCIPLE.
- OF COURSE WE'RE HER ALLIES!
- SO YOU'RE DARK PRIESTESSES.
I WON'T SPARE YOU EITHER, THEN.
- UH! A DARK PRIESTESS?
- HOW DARE YOU INSULT US?
- YOU'RE NOT DARK PRIESTESSES?
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
I AM MOMIJI.
- AND I AM BOTAN.
- WE ARE PRIESTESSES
WHO HAVE TRAINED HARD IN
THE ART OF SLAYING DEMONS.
- DON'T EVEN MENTION US
IN THE SAME BREATH
AS A DARK PRIESTESS.
- THEY DON'T REALLY
LOOK LIKE BAD PEOPLE.
- SO THEY'RE NOT
TSUBAKI'S HELPERS?
- SLOW DOWN AND HOLD ON
A MINUTE, YOU TWO.
- SILENCE!
YOUR APPEARANCE TELLS ME
THAT YOU'RE A MONK...
AND YOU A DEMON SLAYER.
AND AS FOR YOU...
- LOOK AT THOSE CLOTHES.
- I SENSE SPIRITUAL POWERS.
- YES, I AGREE.
YOU'RE A PRIESTESS!
- WELL, I GUESS
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
[LAUGHING]
- WHY DO YOU COLLABORATE
WITH DEMONS SUCH AS THESE?
- SO I GET INCLUDED
WITH THE DEMONS?
- WE HAVEN'T DONE ANY HARM
TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE.
[GASP]
- OH, MY!
ISN'T THAT LITTLE FOX ADORABLE?
- ABSOLUTELY CHARMING.
[MEOW]
THAT ONE'S CUTE, TOO.
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
- WHAT, INDEED?
- NOW WHAT, GUYS?
THEY DON'T SEEM
VERY HARMFUL TO ME.
- HMPH!
- WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO
WIN THEM OVER, THAT'S ALL.
HELLO THERE, LADIES!
- I GET IT!
- YOU DEMON! YOU'VE DISGUISED
YOUR APPEARANCE!
- HUH?
[LAUGHING NERVOUSLY]
- BY CHANGING YOUR DISGUSTING
LOOKS, YOU MAY HAVE DECEIVED
SOME POOR FOOLS,
BUT YOU'RE NOT GONNA DECEIVE US.
- YOUR APPEARANCE
CANNOT TRICK US.
- AAH!
WHO, ME?
I'M INNOCENT!
- STOP ACTING SO SCARED, SHIPPO.
IF THEY INSIST ON INTERFERING,
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO USE FORCE.
- CHILL OUT, INUYASHA.
- I'M SURE WE CAN
TALK THIS THING OUT.
- TIME TO TAKE ACTION!
- I AGREE WITH YOU COMPLETELY.
- NOW, NOW, LADIES.
- AAH! OHH!
- MIROKU!
- WHEN DID YOU...?
- HOW DID YOU...?
- IF YOU WILL ALLOW ME,
I CAN EXPLAIN
EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE DOING
WITH THAT DEMON OVER THERE.
YOU SEE, IT ALL ORIGINATED
WITH THE SACRED JEWEL.
THE DEMONS COVETED
THE POWER IT HELD.
- UH...UH...
AAH!
[CLANG]
- WHY, YOU LITTLE PERVERT!
- YOU'VE GONE AND SOLD YOUR SOUL
TO THE DEMON, HAVEN'T YOU?
[SIGH]
- IT'S THE HAND.
IT'S POSSESSED BY A DEMON.
- YOU'RE POSSESSED BY SOMETHING,
BUT IT AIN'T A DEMON.
- WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
WE'RE TRYING TO GET
SOMEWHERE WITH THEM.
- MY POINT EXACTLY.
HOW SAD.
- IS TSUBAKI OVER THERE?
- YOU WILL NOT PASS!
GO!
[SCREECHING]
- OK.
- SHIKIGAMI.
THESE SPIRIT PUPPETS
HAVE BEEN GIVEN SOULS
WHICH THEY THEN CONTROL.
- HMPH!
UNH!
- LOOK HOW WEAK THEY ARE.
- YOU CAN'T REALLY TAKE
THESE THINGS SERIOUSLY.
- THAT'S FOR SURE.
[SHRIEKING]
- THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE
WORK, YOU DEMONS.
- THAT WAS ALL PART
OF OUR TRICK...
- IN ORDER TO GET THESE STRANDS
OF YOUR HAIR FROM YOU.
[GASP]
- NOW I UNDERSTAND.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAEDE?
- THEY INTEND TO TRANSPOSE US
INTO THOSE SHIKIGAMI.
- VERY CLEVER, OLD DEMON.
- I AM A PRIESTESS!
- BUT WHOSE BODIES
ARE THEY GONNA BE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I'LL SMASH THEM APART,
NO MATTER WHO THEY ARE!
- WHAT IS THAT?
- IT CAN'T BE!
- I THINK PERHAPS IT CAN.
- THAT'S INUYASHA!
- IT AIN'T NOTHING LIKE ME.
- IF THAT'S HIM, THEN DON'T
TELL ME THIS IS GONNA BE...
- I'M AFRAID SO.
- ME, TOO.
- ME, THREE!
IT'S NOT EXACTLY
LIKE HER, THOUGH.
- AAH!
I DON'T LOOK LIKE THAT BLIMP!
- THIS CEREMONY OF YOURS
IS QUITE ELABORATE.
IS THE SEAL TRULY THAT STRONG?
- THIS PARTICULAR CEREMONY
IS MERELY TO OPEN THE DOOR.
THERE ARE EVEN STRONGER
SEALS FURTHER IN.
- OH?
- HA HA!
I THINK THAT WE'VE
OUTDONE OURSELVES.
- THEY'RE ADORABLE.
ARE YOU SURPRISED, DEMONS?
- THESE SHIKIGAMI DON'T MERELY
LOOK LIKE BOTH OF YOU.
YOUR POWER HAS BEEN
TRANSFERRED INTACT.
- LOOKS NOTHING LIKE ME!
- YEAH, ME, EITHER!
- GO!
- THIS IS GETTING STUPID.
IRON REAPER, SOUL STEALER!
[GARBLED]
- IRON REAPER, SOUL STEALER!
- UNH!
HUH? UNH!
UNH! STAY OUT OF
THE WAY, KAGOME!
- WOULD YOU STOP CALLING
THAT THING MY NAME?
[GRUNTING]
IF THAT SHIKIGAMI IS
SUPPOSED TO BE INUYASHA...
SIT!
- UNH!
AAAHH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, KAGOME?!
- OOPS!
- IT SEEMS THAT THE POWERS
OF THE ITEMS THEY ARE CARRYING
ARE NOT TRANSFERRED.
- GOES TO PROVE THAT
THING'S A BIG FAKE.
FAKE--BUT KIND OF ENVIABLE.
HA! WHAT'S WITH THAT SWORD?
YOU'RE FINISHED!
AAH!
HYAH!
KAGOME, DO SOMETHING
ABOUT KAGOME!
- WOULD YOU STOP CALLING
THAT THING MY NAME?!
BESIDES, WHY DON'T YOU DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT INUYASHA?!
- THAT THING AIN'T ME!
- THEY SEEM TO BE
MISSING THE POINT.
- WE'D BETTER TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- JUST WHAT I WAS GONNA SUGGEST.
[GROWLING]
THIS ISN'T GONNA BE EASY.
- MIROKU, CAN YOU TAKE CARE
OF, UH, KAGOME?
- STOP CALLING
THAT BEAST KAGOME!
- NO, I THINK I WOULD RATHER
TAKE CARE OF INUYASHA.
- THAT THING'S NOT ME!
- ME, TOO. I COULD
FIGHT INUYASHA WITHOUT
ANY SECOND THOUGHTS.
- YEP.
- HEY, WHAT DO YOU TWO
MEAN BY THAT?!
- IT'S NOT PERSONAL.
- OUT OF MY WAY, YOU TWO!
I'M GONNA FINISH BOTH OF THEM
OFF WITH MY WIND SCAR!
YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
- AH!
- UNH!
- I CAN'T...I CAN'T MOVE!
- EXACTLY, DEMON!
WE'LL RENDER YOU ALL PARALYZED.
- UNH!
[GASP]
- SHIPPO!
- BUT THAT CUTE LITTLE ONE IS
IN PAIN, AS WELL.
- HE MUST BE STOPPED.
HE'S A DEMON, TOO.
- THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU TWO.
- OH, NO! THAT DEMON
IS STILL MOVING!
- GO!
- WE'RE GOING.
- IF YOU GET IN OUR WAY,
WE'LL SLAY YOU, AS WELL.
- WOULD YOU TWO STOP THIS?
WE HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
WRONG, LET ALONE WORTH
BEING KILLED OVER.
- MIROKU, WE MUST SUBDUE THOSE
TWO PRIESTESSES FIRST.
- YES, I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT.
UNH!
- DON'T YOU DARE
INTERFERE WITH US!
- WHY, YOU...
ENOUGH...ALREADY!
[GRUNTING]
IF YOU DON'T CUT IT OUT...
- STUBBORN DEMON.
- WE WON'T BE DEFEATED.
- YOU THERE!
- HMM?
- COMING IN!
UNH!
- AAH!
- HEY, YOU GUYS,
I CAN MOVE AGAIN!
[GRUNTING]
- YOU'RE...THROUGH!
[COUGHING]
WIND SCAR!
- AAH!
- SO MUCH FOR THEM.
- NAH, THEY'VE JUST
FAINTED, THAT'S ALL.
FEAR NOT. THEIR LIVES
AREN'T IN DANGER,
AND THEY DON'T SEEM TO BE HURT.
AAH!
[SIGH]
- WHAT'LL WE DO WITH THESE TWO?
- KAGOME, DO YOU THINK
THEY'LL ATTACK US AGAIN
WHEN THEY COME TO?
- TSUBAKI MUST HAVE
EITHER SWEET-TALKED THEM
OR DECEIVED THEM.
IN ANY CASE, I THINK
THEY'D UNDERSTAND
IF WE EXPLAINED
OURSELVES TO THEM.
- RIGHT. AND WHO'S GONNA
TAKE ON SUCH A SILLY TASK?
- NATURALLY, I WILL
HAVE TO HANDLE THIS.
- HUH?
- I WILL TAKE THEM BOTH INTO
CUSTODY AND STAY WITH THEM
UNTIL EVERYTHING IS IN THE OPEN.
- HEY, SHIPPO, WILL YOU STAY
HERE WITH MIROKU, PLEASE?
- WHO, ME? WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO WITH MIROKU?
- ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
KEEP AN EYE ON THE MONK.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
AND IF YOU'RE HERE, IT'LL
BE EASIER TO CONVINCE THEM
THAT YOU'RE NOT EVIL.
- I'LL HAVE TO BE ON MY TOES.
- KIRARA, YOU STAY, TOO.
- YOU DO WHAT YOU WANT.
I'M GOING AFTER TSUBAKI.
- WAIT, INUYASHA!
- AAH!
[GROANING]
- WAIT UNTIL I BRING
DOWN THE BARRIER.
- IT WILL BE OPEN SOON.
- WHAT'S INSIDE
THAT TOWER ANYWAY?
- A DEMON.
- 100 YEARS AGO, THE HEAD PRIEST
LOST MANY OF HIS MEN,
AND IT WAS ALL HE COULD DO
TO SEAL THIS FEARSOME DEMON
IN THIS TOWER.
- YOU MEAN, A TERRIBLE
DEMON IS INSIDE?
- YES, AND EACH GENERATION MAKES
SURE THE DOOR REMAINS SEALED.
TSUBAKI, IN TIME,
THIS DUTY WILL BE YOURS.
- I UNDERSTAND, MASTER.
- YOU MUST NEVER OPEN THE DOOR
OF THE FORBIDDEN TOWER, TSUBAKI.
- THE DEMON SEALED INSIDE
HAS ENORMOUS POWERS.
- YOU INTEND TO USE THE SACRED
JEWEL TO MAKE HIM OBEY YOU?
- YES, I WILL INDEED.
I REFUSE TO GIVE IN YET.
- HEY! I SEE SOMETHING UP AHEAD!
- I SENSE THE SACRED
JEWEL NEARBY.
- DO YOU THINK
TSUBAKI'S IN THERE?
- HMPH!
UNH!
[GRUNTING]
WHAT IS THIS?
- INUYASHA!
- EVEN THE GATE TO THE SHRINE
HAS A BARRIER.
[GRUNTING]
- UNH!
- HE BROKE THROUGH THAT BARRIER?
- SHOW YOURSELF, TSUBAKI!
HUH?
- HUH?
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- WHY? WHY DID I LOSE TO KIKYO?
- WHAT'S WITH THAT TOWER?
IS THAT WHERE TSUBAKI
HAS ESCAPED TO?
- WHAT IS IT THAT I AM LACKING?
- THAT'S KAGURA.
SO NARAKU AND TSUBAKI
ARE WORKING TOGETHER!
- OH, DEMON, IF YOU DESIRE
THE SACRED JEWEL,
YOU WILL OBEY ME!
- NEXT TIME, "GIANT OGRE
OF THE FORBIDDEN TOWER."
- I WILL HAVE ETERNAL LIFE!