>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> MOUNT HAKUREI OVERFLOWS WITH
A DEMONIC AURA, AND NARAKU'S
PRESENCE SEEMS VERY CLOSE.
IN ORDER TO REACH HIM, INUYASHA
FACES A FINAL CONFRONTATION WITH
BANKOTSU.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE--"INUYASHA."
>> UNH!
>> HYAH!
>> IRON REVERSE SOULSTEALER!
>> HA HA HA!
>> HUH?
AAH!
UNH!
>> I AM BANKOTSU, LEADER OF THE
BAND OF 7, AND I'VE NEVER LOST A
BATTLE TO ANYONE.
>> ERR.
[GRUNTING]
>> MIROKU, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YES, MORE OR LESS.
THE REMAINS OF DEMONS.
SANGO, LOWER ME DOWN SOME MORE.
IS THIS ALL NARAKU'S DOING?
>> UNH!
YOU UNDERESTIMATE MY STRENGTH.
THERE WAS A GOOD REASON I BECAME
THE LEADER OF THE BAND OF 7!
>> UNH!
AAH!
>> I CONTROLLED A GANG OF
MURDERERS WITH MY OWN POWER LONG
BEFORE I WAS RESURRECTED BY THE
SHIKON JEWEL!
>> HUH?
AAH!
>> HUH.
YOU REALLY ARE PATHETIC.
>> ONE OF YOUR JEWEL SHARDS,
IT'S IMBEDDED IN YOUR LEFT ARM.
THAT'S A PRETTY STRAIGHTFORWARD
WAY TO USE THEM, ESPECIALLY
CONSIDERING HOW TWISTED YOU ARE.
>> HA.
SO YOU LET ME HIT YOU ON PURPOSE
TO CHECK ME OUT.
WILL YOU TAKE MY SHARDS FROM ME,
OR WILL I PULL THAT HEAD OF
YOURS CLEAN OFF?
WHO'S GONNA BE FIRST?
[SCREECHING]
>> TAKE THAT AND THAT.
>> MASTER JAKEN, LOOK AT THE
SKY!
>> HUH?
HUH?
LOOK, LORD SESSHOMARU.
THE DEMONS ARE MAKING THEIR
ESCAPE.
HUH?
AREN'T YOU GOING AFTER THEM?
>> THEY'RE INSIGNIFICANT.
[GROWLING]
>> DID NARAKU SET THEM FREE ON
PURPOSE, OR HAS HE NO USE FOR
THEM ANYMORE?
IN ANY CASE, I SHALL GO SEE FOR
MYSELF.
>> IS THIS WHERE NARAKU'S
HIDING?
SENSE ANYTHING KAGOME?
>> YES.
I SENSE JEWEL SHARDS, AND
THEY'RE SOMEWHERE DEEP INSIDE
THIS CAVE.
>> WE'RE GOING IN?
>> WE HAVE TO.
>> I THOUGHT SO.
OH, YEAH!
DON'T WE HAVE TO WAY FOR HOKAKU
AND GINTA?
HUH?
>> WE CAN'T BE WAITING AROUND
FOR THEM.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'D BETTER GET GOING.
>> COME ON.
>> AAH!
WAIT!
I'M NOT READY FOR THIS YET!
>> WE HAVE TO HURRY.
THE SHARDS ARE BECOMING MORE AND
MORE TAINTED.
>> LOOK AT THEM ALL.
>> NOW WE KNOW FOR CERTAIN THAT
NARAKU WAS REBUILDING HIMSELF
INSIDE THIS CHAMBER.
>> THEN THAT MEANS THESE
DEMONS--
>> THEY WERE PROBABLY USED TO
CREATE PARTS OF NARAKU'S BODY.
HUH?
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT'S MOVING.
>> THERE'S MORE OF THEM, TOO!
>> UGH!
INCREDIBLE.
>> I KNOW.
THEY AREN'T DEMONS.
MORE LIKE CLUMPS OF FLESH.
>> YES.
IT'S AS THOUGH THEY'RE ABOUT TO
SPAWN SOMETHING.
>> SPAWN?
BUT WHAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HUH?
WHERE DID NARAKU ESCAPE TO?
>> WHY, YOU!
UNH!
HE BLOCKED ME.
>> HUH.
AAH!
UNH!
>> AAH!
AAH!
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
I'M GOING OUT OF MY WAY TO PUNCH
WITH THIS HAND TO MAKE IT EASIER
FOR YOU TO TAKE MY JEWEL SHARDS.
WHAT?
IS THIS BATTLE OVER ALREADY?
HUH!
PATHETIC.
THIS IS A REAL DISAPPOINTMENT,
AND HERE I WAS CONVINCED THAT
YOU'D PUT UP MUCH MORE OF A
FIGHT.
DON'T WORRY, THOUGH, INUYASHA.
I'M NOT INTERESTED IN TORMENTING
SOMEONE AS FEEBLE AS YOU.
WEAKLINGS HOLD NO APPEAL FOR ME.
NOW, DIE!
DAMN YOU TO HELL.
>> I'M NOT LIKE ALL THE OTHER
HUMANS AND DEMONS YOU'VE
SLAUGHTERED.
I CAN TAKE A LOT MORE DAMAGE
THAN THEM.
>> UNH!
AAH!
>> I'VE GOT 5 OF THEM.
ONCE I GET THE SHARD IN YOUR
LEFT ARM, IT WILL BE OVER FOR
YOU, BANKOTSU.
>> SILENCE, FOOL.
I WILL NEVER DIE.
I'LL KILL YOU AND TAKE BACK THE
JEWEL SHARDS YOU STOLE FROM ME.
>> DON'T COUNT ON IT.
I'VE GOT NEWS.
GETTING OUT OF HERE IS ONLY HALF
THE PROBLEM.
NARAKU WILL NEVER LET YOU STAY
ALIVE IF YOU POSSESS THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS.
>> I'M SURE HE'S MORE INTERESTED
IN KILLING YOU.
>> OVER THERE.
[GROWLING AND HISSING]
THOSE DEMONS AREN'T GUARDS.
THEY INTEND TO GO AFTER WHOEVER
SURVIVES.
>> DAMN THAT NARAKU.
>> I'VE NO IDEA WHAT KIND OF
PROMISE YOU MADE WITH NARAKU
WHEN HE REVIVED YOU.
>> AWAKEN, BANKOTSU, AWAKEN.
I GRANT YOU LIFE ONCE AGAIN.
I WANT YOU TO SERVE ME,
BANKOTSU.
IF YOU DO, THEN THIS RENEWED
LIFE OF YOURS WILL BE
EVERLASTING.
NOW, GO FORTH WITH YOUR 6
COMRADES AND DESTROY MY ENEMIES.
>> NARAKU USED YOU AND THE BAND
OF 7.
YOU WERE NOTHING BUT A HUMAN
SHIELD TO GIVE HIM PROTECTION.
>> HA!
SO WHAT IF HE DID USE US?
>> YOU DON'T CARE?
>> THE BAND OF 7 WERE ORIGINALLY
MERCENARIES.
WE WERE HIRED BY CLAN LORDS, AND
THEY DIDN'T GIVE A DAMN ABOUT US
EITHER.
WHEN WE BECAME TOO STRONG AND
DANGEROUS FOR THEM, THEY HUNTED
US DOWN AND CHOPPED OFF OUR
HEADS.
I NEVER TRUSTED NARAKU RIGHT
FROM THE VERY START, BUT NOW I'M
RESURRECTED, I CAN DO AS I
PLEASE.
I'LL KILL ANYONE THAT GETS IN MY
WAY, EVEN IF IT HAPPENS TO BE
NARAKU.
>> REALLY?
NARAKU DIDN'T DO HIMSELF ANY
FAVORS PICKING YOU TO REVIVE.
>> ENOUGH!
WHAT'S YOUR STORY?
HOW DID YOU AWAKEN FROM YOUR
SEAL?
>> NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
>> IT'S ALL ABOUT GREED,
INUYASHA.
WE'RE ALL THE SAME.
THAT DRIED-UP OLD SAINT
HAKUSHIN, THE DEAD PRIESTESS,
EVEN YOU, YOU LIVE ONLY BECAUSE
OF YOUR INSATIABLE HUNGER FOR
LIFE.
DON'T MAKE US OUT TO BE THE ONLY
VILLAINS HERE.
>> YOU'RE THE ONES WHO KILLED
COUNTLESS PEOPLE, NOT US!
>> YEAH, AND WE'VE KILLED OUR
SHARE OF DEMONS, TOO.
>> HUH?
OH, NO!
THERE ARE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
IMBEDDED IN BANRYU!
UNH!
HYAH!
HUH?
[GROWLING]
>> HYAH!
THAT'S 991!
992!
993!
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
[GROWLING]
>> COME AND GET ME!
994!
995!
996!
>> HYAH!
>> 997!
998!
999!
[ROARS]
AAH!
ONE...THOUSAND!
HUH!
I DON'T NEED THE REST OF YOU!
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
[SCREECHING]
[PANTING]
IF YOU DECIDE TO GET OUT OF
HERE, I WON'T GET IN YOUR WAY.
>> I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE UNTIL
I KILL YOU AND AVENGE MY
BROTHERS.
>> HA!
JUST BECAUSE YOUR BLADE
TRANSFORMED A LITTLE?
>> ACTUALLY, I WANTED TO LOP
YOUR HEAD OFF TO COMPLETE THE
TRANSFORMATION, BUT THEN AGAIN,
IT MAY NOT HAVE BEEN ENOUGH,
YOU BEING ONLY A HALF-DEMON.
>> WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
>> YOU'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT!
>> WHY IS THAT SWORD SO
POWERFUL?
IT'S LIKE SESSHOMARU'S SWORD
TOKIJIN!
>> WHEN I FIRST MET NARAKU, HE
TOLD ME ABOUT THE EXISTENCE OF
THE SHIKON JEWEL, A SACRED JEWEL
THAT COULD EMPOWER BOTH HUMANS
AND DEMONS.
HUMANS CAN'T POSSESS DEMON
POWERS, AND I DIDN'T CARE FOR
SPIRITUAL POWERS, AND I WASN'T
BORN WITH THE POWER OF THE
DEVINE.
>> AAH!
UNH!
>> I ALWAYS THOUGHT THAT TO
BECOME POWERFUL YOU HAD TO MAKE
YOURSELF STRONGER.
HOWEVER, THERE WAS ONE OTHER
WAY, AND THAT'S TO PUT POWER
INTO AN OBJECT, SO I MADE A WISH
ON MY BANRYU.
I'VE CUT OF THE HEADS OF 1,000
WARLORDS.
>> WIND SCAR!
>> AND JUST NOW I KILLED MY
THOUSANDTH DEMON!
>> MY WIND SCAR!
>> BESIDES THE WISH I MADE ON
IT, BANRYU HAS SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS INSIDE.
1,000 HUMANS, 1,000 DEMONS.
THIS DEMON SWORD THAT HAS
ABSORBED THE WRATH OF 2,000
LIVES.
YOU WIELD A DEMON SWORD, TOO,
BUT CAN IT BEAT MY BANRYU?
UNH!
>> YOU WERE RESURRECTED BY
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS ALL RIGHT,
BUT YOU'RE STILL HUMAN.
THAT SWORD IS SURROUNDED BY A
DEMONIC AURA.
GET RID OF IT FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
>> GO TO HELL, HALF-BREED!
>> AAH!
>> A DEMON CAN NEVER UNDERSTAND
MY DESIRES!
OR MAYBE YOU THINK YOU
UNDERSTAND BECAUSE YOU'RE
HALF-DEMON.
IS THAT IT?
YOU CAN'T UNDERSTAND MAN'S
WORLD, WHERE STRENGTH IS YOUR
ONLY HOPE OF SURVIVAL.
IT'S OVER.
>> HUH?
HUH?
AN AURA.
>> WITH THIS POWER, I WILL LOSE
TO NO ONE!
AAH!
>> BANKOTSU ISN'T A DEMON, BUT
IF BANRYU'S PRODUCING THIS
DEMONIC AURA, I CAN USE THE
BACKLASH WAVE.
BACKLASH WAVE!
>> AAH!
UNH!
AAH!
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
>> BACKLASH WAVE!
>> AAH!
UNH!
AAH!
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
[PANTING]
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> YOU WERE WAY TOO GREEDY,
BANKOTSU.
YOU WERE STRONG ENOUGH ON YOUR
OWN, EVEN WITHOUT THE JEWEL
SHARDS.
>> HA.
HA HA HA!
[BOOM]
>> HUH?
WHOA!
HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> LOOK, MIROKU.
>> NOW WHAT?
WHOA!
RUN FOR IT.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> UNH!
>> WE'LL FIND OUT SOON ENOUGH.
>> THE DEMONIC AURA IS GROWING
STRONGER.
>> RIN.
>> YES?
>> TAKE AUN AND GET AWAY FROM
THE MOUNTAIN.
>> HUH?
WHAT WILL YOU DO, LORD
SESSHOMARU?
>> IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING.
NARAKU IS IN THERE SOMEWHERE.
>> PARDON ME, MILORD.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> IF THERE'S NO QUESTION THAT
NARAKU HAS KEPT HIMSELF HIDDEN
FROM HIS ENEMIES UNTIL NOW IN
ORDER TO RECOUP HIS STRENGTH,
HE HAS UNDOUBTEDLY GROWN MUCH
STRONGER THAN HE WAS SINCE THE
LAST TIME WE MET.
>> YOUR POINT IS?
>> DAAH?!
MY POINT, YES, WHAT WAS MY
POINT?
NAAH!
I SUPPOSE MY MIND'S GROWING
WEAKER WITH AGE.
HA HA!
HMM?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU?
GOOD LUCK, MILORD.
[GRUNTING]
DAMN!
WHAT'S WITH THIS GROUND?
IT'S TRYING TO DRAW ME IN, AND
IT'S NOT ONLY THE GROUND EITHER.
THIS ENTIRE CAVE LOOKS LIKE A
GIANT WALL OF FLESH.
HUH?
UNH!
I CAN'T MOVE.
[GRUNTING]
>> HUH?
[THUMPING]
SOMETHING'S GOING ON.
IT'S GETTING LOUDER IN HERE.
LET'S HURRY, KAGOME.
HUH?
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
KOGA!
>> DAMN IT!
WHAT IS THIS?
[GROWLS]
>> TAKE MY HAND, KOGA!
>> IS IT...
[GRUNTING]
>> PLEASE, KOGA, HANG ON!
>> YOU CAN DO IT!
>> LET GO, KAGOME.
>> HUH?
AAH!
>> I'D NEVER PUT YOU IN DANGER.
>> KOGA!
>> DON'T!
THIS IS DEFINITELY...
>> KOGA!
WHAT IS THIS STUFF?
IT'S NOT STONE.
>> LOOK, KAGOME!
>> THIS ENTIRE CAVE IS CHANGING.
>> IT'S LIKE BEING INSIDE THE
BELLY OF A LIVING BEING.
UNH!
KAGOME, ARE WE GONNA BE
DEVOURED, AS WELL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IF THAT WAS GONNA HAPPEN,
WOULDN'T WE HAVE ALREADY BEEN
EATEN?
IN ANY CASE, LET'S GO AFTER
KOGA.
WE CAN'T LEAVE HIM.
>> UNH!
KAGOME, WE DON'T KNOW WHERE HE'S
BURIED!
>> I KNOW WHERE HE IS!
I CAN SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS IN HIS LEGS.
THEY'RE MOVING INSIDE THESE
FLESHY WALLS, AND THEY'RE
HEADING STRAIGHT AHEAD TOWARD
NARAKU'S TAINTED JEWEL SHARDS.
[GRUNTING]
>> DAMN IT!
[PANTING]
>> WE CLEARED THE TUNNEL!
>> YEAH!
NOW WHAT?
WHERE HAVE WE ENDED UP?
>> UH, KAGOME, WHAT'S THAT?
>> HUH?
>> ARE THEY DEMONS?
>> NO, THEY SEEM DIFFERENT
SOMEHOW.
>> WHATEVER THEY ARE, THEY GIVE
ME THE CREEPS.
>> WHO'S THERE?
KAGOME, SHIPPO, IS THAT YOU?
>> MIROKU, SANGO!
>> KAGOME!
>> IS IT JUST YOU TWO?
WHERE'S INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
YOU MEAN HE'S NOT WITH YOU?
>> HE WENT AFTER YOU AND ENTERED
MOUNT HAKUREI AHEAD OF US!
>> WE HAVEN'T CROSSED PATHS.
>> WHERE COULD HE HAVE GOTTEN
TO?
>> INUYASHA.
[BOOM]
OHH!
>> WHOA!
>> AAH!
>> CATCH THEM, KIRARA!
>> WHOA!
>> THANK YOU, KIRARA.
>> WHERE'S KAGOME?
>> DON'T WORRY.
I GOT YOU, KAGOME.
>> THANKS.
>> SOMETHING'S RISING UP FROM
THE CAVERN.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
INUYASHA, WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS OF THE
BAND OF 7 HAVE BEEN TAKEN BACK
BY NARAKU!
>> SO YOU FINALLY MADE YOUR
MOVE, NARAKU!
>> IT HAS BEGUN, BUT IT WILL END
QUICKLY.
>> IS THAT--
>> IT'S NARAKU'S NEW BODY.
>> INUYASHA, YOU AND YOUR
FRIENDS WILL DIE HERE, FOR I NOW
POSSESS A NEW BODY.
>> NARAKU HAS REAPPEARED AT
LAST, BUT WHAT IS HE REALLY
AFTER?
NEXT TIME, "BEYOND THE
DARKNESS--NARAKU REBORN."
>> ONLY ONE THING REMAINS TO BE
DEALT WITH--KIKYO.