- IT'S APPROACHING!
FROM THE FOREST!
DEMON SLAYER, IT'S TIME!
- [CROWD MURMURS]
- HA!
A SHARD OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
I THOUGHT SO.
- SLAYER,
WHAT IS THAT?
- THE CAUSE OF
THE CENTIPEDE'S FEROCITY.
MY JOB HERE IS DONE.
CALL AGAIN FOR ME
SHOULD YOU REQUIRE HELP.
- BUT--BUT WE HAVEN'T YET
PAID YOU A FEE.
- I SHALL TAKE THIS JEWEL SHARD
AS PAYMENT.
IT ONLY MAKES SENSE,
SEEING AS IT ORIGINATED
FROM MY HOME VILLAGE.
- TONIGHT THE SKY
IS FULL OF STARS.
SOMETIMES I WONDER
WHICH THERE ARE MORE OF--
STARS IN THE SKY OR SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
OUR SEARCH IS FAR
FROM ENDED YET.
- NOT NECESSARILY, SHIPPO.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THE DEMON NARAKU
IS GATHERING SHARDS OF THE JEWEL
JUST AS WE ARE.
IN THE LONG RUN, HE'LL SAVE US
A GREAT DEAL OF WORK.
HE'LL GET THE JEWEL SHARDS,
AND THEN WE WILL GET HIM!
HOW DOES THAT SOUND
FOR A GOOD STRATEGY?
- INUYASHA, WITH EVERY SHARD
THAT NARAKU GATHERS,
HE BECOMES STRONGER,
DOES HE NOT?
- HA! HUH?
- IN THAT CASE, WE'LL NEVER
BE ABLE TO CAPTURE HIM.
IT'S OBVIOUS.
OUR ONLY HOPE IS TO FIND
MORE JEWELS THAN HE DOES.
UHH! EVEN A LITTLE KID
LIKE ME
CAN FIGURE OUT SOMETHING
THAT SIMPLE.
IT MAKES ME WONDER
IF MAYBE YOU HAVEN'T TAKEN
A FEW TOO MANY BLOWS
TO THE HEAD.
- LET ME TRY THAT THEORY
OUT ON YOU!
- INUYASHA,
WHAT WILL YOU DO
IF YOU GATHER ALL THE SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL?
- WHAT ELSE? I'LL BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED, BONA FIDE DEMON.
- OH. THAT'S WHAT
YOU HAVE PLANNED.
- NOBODY WANTS TO BE
A WEAKLING, RIGHT?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE ABLE TO STAND
UP TO SOMEONE YOU DON'T LIKE
IF YOU NEED TO.
- TELL ME SOMETHING, THOUGH.
WHEN YOU USE THE POWER
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
TO BECOME A TRUE DEMON,
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK YOU
WILL REMAIN AS YOU ARE NOW?
- UH, WHY WOULDN'T I?
- WELL, THEN, CAN YOU RECALL
EVER HAVING SEEN A DEMON
THAT WAS USING THE SHIKON JEWEL
SHARDS FOR A BENEVOLENT END?
THIS IS MERELY A THEORY,
BUT I BELIEVE THAT THOSE
WHO SEEK OUT
AND GAIN THE POWERS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
EVENTUALLY LOSE THEIR OWN HEARTS
IN THE PROCESS.
- HUH.
THAT MAY BE SO,
BUT WHEN DID I EVER SAY
I WANTED TO BE A GOOD DEMON?
- YOU DIDN'T, BUT YOU DO WISH
TO PROTECT KAGOME,
AND THAT IS WHY
YOU DESIRE MORE POWER.
INUYASHA, ONCE YOU BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON,
WHO'S TO SAY YOU WON'T DEVOUR
SHIPPO AND KAGOME?
- HUH?
- WHY ME?
WOULDN'T YOU BE TASTIER?
- I WILL HAVE FLED
LONG BEFORE.
- HE'S WRONG.
ALL THE DEMONS I'VE FOUGHT UNTIL
NOW WERE ROTTEN FROM THE START.
IT'S A MERE COINCIDENCE,
THAT'S ALL.
I'M DIFFERENT FROM THEM.
- INUYASHA.
- WHAT? A GIRL TOOK
THE JEWEL SHARD?
WHO WAS SHE?
COME ON, ANSWER ME!
- OH, NO, LOOK!
ANOTHER DEMON!
- CALL FOR THE SLAYERS!
- A GIANT CENTIPEDE!
- I AM NOT A CENTIPEDE!
DEMON SLAYERS,
YOU SAY?
- WOW.
SO, PEOPLE MAKE A LIVING
GOING AROUND SLAYING DEMONS.
- AND THIS DEMON SLAYER
COLLECTED THE JEWEL SHARD
IN LIEU OF PAYMENT, YOU SAY?
- AYE. SHE SAID THAT THIS SACRED
SOMETHING-OR-OTHER JEWEL
ORIGINATED FROM HER HOME VILLAGE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- AYE.
- HUH?
- INUYASHA, HAVE YOU HEARD
OF THE JEWEL'S ORIGINS?
- NOT AT ALL.
WHEN I LEARNED
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
OF THE 4 SOULS,
KIKYO HELD IT
IN HER PROTECTION.
I HAD NEVER GIVEN ANY THOUGHT
TO WHERE THE JEWEL CAME FROM
OR HOW IT WAS CREATED.
- HELLO, SANGO.
WELCOME HOME.
- THANK YOU.
- WHAT WAS YOUR PREY?
- A GIANT CENTIPEDE.
I DIDN'T BRING MUCH
EXCEPT SOME HIDE AND LEGS.
WE COULD USE IT
TO MAKE SOME ARMOR.
HA HA! HELLO, KIRARA!
I HOPE YOU'VE BEEN
A GOOD KITTY.
- WELCOME HOME, SANGO.
- HELLO, MY DEAR BROTHER.
- FATHER SAID TO...
UH, THE LORD WISHES TO SEE YOU.
- I SEE.
SO YOU MANAGED TO BRING HOME
A SHARD OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
WELL DONE, SANGO.
- TELL ME, FATHER,
WILL PRAYER SUPPRESS THE EVIL
WITHIN THE SHARD?
- IT IS UNLIKELY.
- I DIDN'T THINK SO.
- 50 YEARS PAST,
THE JEWEL WAS SUPPOSEDLY
GIVEN TO A YOUNG PRIESTESS
WITH UNUSUAL POWERS
FOR PURIFICATION.
BUT IN THE END,
EVEN THAT MAIDEN
BECAME EMBROILED
IN A FIGHT OVER THE JEWEL
AND PAID FOR IT
WITH HER LIFE.
UNTIL WE ARE ABLE TO FIND
SOMEONE WHO HAS THE POWER
TO PURIFY THE JEWEL,
ALL WE CAN HOPE TO DO
IS GATHER THE FRAGMENTS
AND KEEP A CLOSE WATCH
OVER THEM.
- THE POWER TO PURIFY
THE JEWEL.
- REST YOURSELF, SANGO.
WE'LL BE NEEDING YOU AGAIN
IN A SHORT TIME.
- YES, FATHER.
- KOHAKU, YOU, TOO,
MUST PREPARE FOR BATTLE.
- WHO, UH, ME?
- YES. YOU ARE 11 NOW,
PLENTY OLD ENOUGH
TO GO INTO BATTLE.
- MM...MM-HMM.
SANGO?
- YES?
- DO DEMONS BREATHE FIRE
AND TOXINS AS THEY SAY?
- SOMETIMES.
- THEN IT'S TRUE.
- KOHAKU, WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU SCARED?
- NO, I NEVER SAID
I WAS SCARED.
HUH...
- YOU'LL BE FINE.
WE EXTERMINATE SNAKES
AND SPIDERS AND OTHER
SUCH LARGE BEASTS.
AS FATHER SAYS,
THE MOST FRIGHTENING DEMON
IS ONE THAT MASQUERADES
AS A HUMAN BEING.
HE SAYS THAT IF THAT
TYPE OF DEMON COMES
TO POSSESS THE JEWEL,
THEN IT'S TROUBLE.
- HMM.
[THUNDER]
- YOU HAVE DONE US WELL TO COME
TO OUR AID, SLAYERS.
WE HAVE BEEN PLAGUED
WITH NIGHTLY VISITS
FROM A GIANT SPIDER
WHICH HAS DEVOURED
SEVERAL OF OUR PEOPLE.
CAN YOU PUT A STOP TO IT?
- FEAR NOT, SIR.
I HAVE BROUGHT ALONG
MY BEST PEOPLE TO SERVE YOU.
- OH?
PERHAPS THEY ARE SKILLED,
BUT I SEE YOU HAVE
BROUGHT ALONG A GIRL
AND EVEN A YOUNG CHILD.
- YES, MY LORD.
THEY ARE MY SON
AND DAUGHTER
AND THE FINEST SLAYERS
IN MY VILLAGE.
WITNESS THEIR SKILLS
FOR YOURSELF IF YOU WOULD.
- HEAR THAT, KOHAKU?
NOW, DO YOUR BEST.
- MM-HMM.
FATHER TELLS A LIE.
HUH?
- MY LORD, IT APPROACHES.
- GO FORTH, DEMON SLAYERS.
- AYE. MOVE OUT.
- [ROARING]
- THE DEMON HAS ARRIVED,
I GATHER.
- YES, MY LORD.
I FEAR IT'S THIS VERY SAME DEMON
WHICH PROLONGS YOUR ILLNESS.
BUT A NUMBER OF DEMON SLAYERS
HAVE BEEN CALLED,
AND TONIGHT WE HOPE TO SEE
THE LAST OF THIS BEAST.
THEN I CAN ONLY PRAY
FOR YOUR SPEEDY RECOVERY.
- DEMON SLAYERS?
- SURROUND IT!
- UH...AAH!
- KOHAKU!
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
- UH-HUH.
- [SHOUTING]
IT'S DOWN! I HAVE IT!
- COMING IN!
- SANGO IS INCREDIBLE!
- THEY CLAIM THAT SHE IS
THE BEST IN THE VILLAGE.
- SHE BROUGHT THE DEMON DOWN
IN ONE SWEEP.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S FINISH THIS UP.
- OFF WITH HIS HEAD!
- THIS IS WHERE I COME IN.
- FOR A DEMON SO LARGE,
IT WAS EASY BRINGING IT DOWN.
- IT WAS TOO EASY.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT THIS
SPIDER THAT RINGS FALSE. HUH?
- WAAH!
- UHH!
- [GASPS]
- AAH! OHH!
- HUH?
- WHY?
KOHAKU, WHY DID YOU SLAY FATHER
AND THE OTHERS?
NO, DON'T, KOHAKU!
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
WHO I AM?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
HALT, LAD!
- STOP THIS MADNESS.
- LET HIM CONTINUE.
IT SHOULD PROVE TO BE
ENTERTAINING.
- WHY DO YOU DO THIS, KOHAKU?
[GRUNTING]
A WEB. A SPIDER WEB.
- [LAUGHS]
- HE'S THE ONE.
[GRUNTS]
YOU DID THIS TO HIM!
YOU'RE FINISHED!
- THE SIBLINGS HAVE TAKEN LEAVE
OF THEIR SENSES.
SLAY THEM.
[GRUNTING]
- SANGO, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
- KOHAKU...
- NO!
SANGO!
- [GASPS]
- TAKE AIM AND CAST YOUR ARROWS
AT THE CRAZED SIBLINGS.
- KOHAKU...
- HELP ME, SANGO.
I'M SO AFRAID.
- DO NOT WORRY.
I AM RIGHT HERE WI--AAH!
UHH...
- A DEATHBED TRUCE
BETWEEN SIBLINGS--HOW SWEET.
AAH!
- HUH?
- MY LORD!
- MY LORD, YOU HAVE SLAIN
YOUR FATHER!
- THIS MAN IS NOT MY FATHER.
SEE FOR YOURSELVES.
- SOME KIND OF BEAST!
- IT'S A DEMON!
- I HAVE THOUGHT FOR
SOME TIME THAT FATHER
WAS ACTING STRANGELY.
CLEARLY, HE WAS POSSESSED
BY THE DEMON.
IT'S A SHAME THAT
THE SLAYERS
WERE SACRIFICED.
BURY THEM IN A CORNER
OF THE GARDEN.
- YES, MY LORD.
- WE MUST BE GETTING CLOSE.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT NO ONE COULD TELL US
WHERE THE SLAYERS
WERE FROM.
- "SOMEWHERE IN THE MOUNTAINS"
WASN'T TOO HELPFUL.
- STOP COMPLAINING.
LET'S JUST FIND IT.
- INUYASHA, DO YOU PLAN ON
STEALING THE SHIKON JEWEL
FRAGMENTS FROM THE VILLAGE?
- YEAH. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- LET'S JUST HOPE THEY DON'T
EXTERMINATE US IN THE PROCESS.
- IT COULD HAPPEN, TOO.
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE PROS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO FIND OUT MORE
ABOUT THE SACRED JEWEL
AND HOW IT CAME TO BE.
THE SLAYERS CLAIM IT
ORIGINATED FROM THEIR VILLAGE.
I'M SURE INUYASHA'S
JUST AS ANXIOUS TO KNOW, TOO.
[WIND HOWLING]
- THIS WIND IS STRANGE.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
- SOMETHING'S APPROACHING
OVERHEAD.
THERE'S A BUNCH OF THEM.
[GASPS]
- A HORDE OF DEMONS!
- THERE MUST BE HUNDREDS
OF THEM.
WHAT ARE THEY?
THEY'RE NO ORDINARY DEMONS.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
THEIR VERY PRESENCE
IS MAKING ME ILL.
- I SMELL DEATH.
THOSE DEMONS ARE CHARGING IN
TO ATTACK.
- WE SHOULD FOLLOW THEM.
- THE SIBLING SLAYERS
WERE STILL SO YOUNG.
- THE POOR THINGS.
- UH!
[GRUNTING]
I'M ALIVE.
I WILL NOT DIE.
- THE WOMAN DEMON SLAYER.
SHE STILL HAS LIFE.
- [LAUGHS]
- [PEOPLE MOANING]
- IT WOULD SEEM YOU HAVE AVENGED
YOUR LONG-HARBORED GRUDGE
AGAINST THE SLAYERS.
AND DID I NOT TELL YOU
THAT THE DEMON SLAYERS WERE NOT
TO BE FOUND AT THIS FORTRESS?
WILL YOU ATTACK ME
AS A FORM OF REBUKE?
HUH.
YES, THAT FEELS MUCH BETTER.
[LAUGHS]
- THE VILLAGE. IT'S BURNED.
- THIS MUST HAVE BEEN THE
VILLAGE THE DEMONS WERE AFTER.
- QUICKLY!
- WAIT UP!
- [KAGOME GASPS]
THIS IS HORRIBLE.
- THE VILLAGERS MUST HAVE
BATTLED WITH THE DEMONS.
- THERE'S NO MISTAKING IT.
THIS IS THE VERY SAME VILLAGE
OF THE DEMON SLAYERS
WE WERE SEEKING.
WHAT IS IT, KAGOME?
- I'M NOT SENSING ANY JEWELS.
THERE ARE NONE.
- NONE ANYMORE.
THEY WERE STOLEN.
- MAYBE IF WE HURRY,
WE CAN CATCH UP WITH THEM.
- WE'LL THINK ABOUT THAT
AFTER WE'VE PROPERLY LAID
THESE PEOPLE TO REST.
THEY DESERVE THAT AT LEAST.
- INUYASHA'S RIGHT.
- SOMETHING IS HERE!
- ONE SURVIVING DEMON.
- LORD INUYASHA,
WOULD THAT BE YOU?
- HUH?
- IT CAN TALK.
- DOWN, KIRARA. THESE PEOPLE
ARE NOT OUR ENEMIES.
- HUH?
- WOW. IT'S SO CUTE.
- [GRUNTING]
AH, HOW I'VE LONGED
FOR THIS NOSE.
- UH! STILL IRRITATING.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- YOU KNOW THIS FLEA?
- IT'S INUYASHA'S VASSAL,
WELL, SORT OF.
- [GRUNTS]
- PRECISELY.
THIS IS THE SECRET VILLAGE
OF THE DEMON SLAYERS.
FOR GENERATIONS, THE PEOPLE
OF THIS VILLAGE HAVE TRAINED
AND WORKED HARD
TO DISPOSE OF DEMONS.
- IT ONLY MAKES SENSE, THEN,
THAT THEY WOULD HAVE BEEN
DESPISED BY THE DEMONS.
- IT IS TRUE, YET IT IS
STRANGE THEY WOULD CHOOSE
THIS TIME TO ATTACK.
A NUMBER OF THEIR WARRIORS
HAD BEEN SUMMONED TO
A DISTANT CASTLE,
AND THIS VILLAGE WAS LEFT
WITH FEW TO PROTECT IT.
I CANNOT HELP BUT WONDER
IF THOSE THAT TRAVELED TO
THE CASTLE ARE INDEED SAFE.
- I AM RELIEVED.
AT LEAST YOU SURVIVED,
YOUNG LADY.
- SLAYER, SHOW THE MASTER
RESPECT WITH A RESPONSE.
- STOP. THAT'S ENOUGH.
- MY LORD.
- YOU SAID YOUR NAME WAS SANGO.
MY DEAR GIRL, YOU HAVE
MY DEEPEST APOLOGIES.
YOU'VE LOST YOUR FAMILY
AND FELLOW VILLAGERS.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW COULD THIS HAVE HAPPENED?
- YOUNG LORD.
- NARAKU.
- YES.
AS YOU COMMANDED,
I RUSHED TO THE VILLAGE
TO NOTIFY THEM
OF THIS TERRIBLE DEVELOPMENT,
BUT THE VILLAGE
HAD ALREADY BEEN ANNIHILATED.
- IT'S A SHAME.
I'D HOPED TO SPEAK TO
SOMEONE AT THE VILLAGE
ABOUT THE SHIKON JEWEL.
- TALK TO ME, MYOGA.
YOU MUST KNOW SOMETHING.
- DO I KNOW SOMETHING?
ABOUT THE SHIKON JEWEL?
- MYOGA, WAS THAT
WHY YOU CAME HERE--
TO FIND OUT MORE ABOUT
THE JEWEL'S ORIGINS?
- YES. IT'S BEEN TROUBLING ME
FOR A GREAT WHILE NOW.
I NEEDED TO KNOW MORE ABOUT
THE HISTORY OF THE JEWEL.
AFTER ALL, EVERYONE
WHO HAS COME ACROSS THE JEWEL
HAS SUFFERED GREAT MISFORTUNE.
I FOLLOWED THE RUMORS
OF THE JEWEL
AND FOUND MYSELF HERE
AT THIS VILLAGE.
HOWEVER, THERE IS STILL
ONE THING THAT DISTURBS ME.
DURING MY JOURNEY,
A WHITE BABOON
CONTINUALLY SLIPPED IN
AND OUT OF MY SIGHT.
- A WHITE BABOON?
- YES.
- IT'S NARAKU.
HE'S CLOSE BY.
- TELL ME EVERYTHING YOU SAW
AT THE VILLAGE
OF THE SLAYERS.
- THE SLAIN BODIES
OF COUNTLESS VILLAGERS
AND THE HALF DEMON
THAT ATTACKED THEM.
HIS NAME IS INUYASHA.
INUYASHA SEEKS THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
TO TRANSFORM HIMSELF
INTO A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
- THE SHIKON JEWEL.
- HE MUST HAVE BELIEVED
THAT HE WOULD FIND THE JEWEL
AT THE VILLAGE,
AND THUS ATTACKED IT.
- SANGO.
- RETURN MY WEAPON...
AND MY ARMOR.
I SHALL AVENGE MY VILLAGE
AND DESTROY THIS INUYASHA
WHO HAS SLAIN MY KIN!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- IN A DESPERATE ATTEMPT
TO AVENGE THE DESTRUCTION
OF HER VILLAGE,
SANGO THE DEMON SLAYER SUMMONS
UP EVERY OUNCE OF HER STRENGTH
TO HUNT DOWN INUYASHA,
WHOM SHE WRONGLY BELIEVES
IS THE PERPETRATOR.
EVEN THIS, IT SEEMS,
IS NARAKU'S DOING.
INUYASHA HUNTS DOWN
THE NEWLY TRANSFORMED NARAKU,
TRYING TO DEFEAT HIM
WITH HIS TETSUSAIGA.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!