- [GROWL]
- TRY ME!
- [MOANING]
- [LAUGHING]
- WHAT'S THIS?
- YOU'VE AWAKENED, I SEE.
- YOU.
- NOW I UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE A HALF DEMON.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA KILL ME,
DO IT NOW.
- DEMON POWER IS GOOD
NOURISHMENT FOR NIMENKA,
THE TREE OF HUMAN-FACED FRUITS.
WITH YOU IN THE BROTH,
IT WILL BEAR THE FRUIT
OF LONGEVITY MORE QUICKLY.
- FORGET IT!
- HURRY AND MAKE YOUR DEMON
POWERS RETURN.
KEEP STRUGGLING.
IF THE THORNS PIERCE YOUR SKIN,
IT WILL BE THAT MUCH EASIER
TO EXTRACT YOUR JUICES.
- DAMN YOU!
HUH?
THAT'S THE BOTTLE KAGOME USED TO
KEEP THE JEWEL SHARDS IN.
TELL ME WHAT YOU'VE
DONE WITH THE OWNER OF
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS!
- OWNER?
I HAVEN'T SEEN ANY OWNER.
I FOUND THESE.
- DON'T PLAY INNOCENT WITH ME.
YOU STOLE THOSE FROM KAGOME.
- KAGOME?
- THE GIRL WHO HAD
THE JEWEL SHARDS!
- A GIRL, YOU SAY?
WHAT TREMENDOUS NEWS!
A GIRL INSIDE MY HOUSE.
- THE DEMON TREE NIMENKA
LOVES WOMEN, TOO,
AND THE YOUNGER, THE BETTER.
HA HA HA!
- KAGOME, I'LL FIND YOU.
JUST KEEP HIDING
TILL I GET TO YOU.
- LET'S SEE.
I FOUND THE SHARDS
SOMEWHERE AROUND HERE.
HUH?
SHE MUST BE
IN MY MINIATURE VILLAGE.
- THAT DOES IT.
KAGOME, EVERYTHING'S
SET OVER HERE.
- ALL RIGHT!
- OK, MOROKU?
- I'M READY WHEN YOU ARE.
- NOW, WHAT COULD THOSE
YOUNGSTERS BE UP TO?
- FIRE!
- [COUGH] IT WORKED!
MOROKU!
- WIND TUNNEL!
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- HERE IT COMES!
- IT WORKED! WE BROKE
THROUGH THE WALL!
[WHINING]
- THERE SHE IS!
- [GASP]
[SCREAM]
- HA HA HA!
FOUND HER.
EXCELLENT.
A YOUNG GIRL.
SHE'S FILTHY, BUT SHE'S SURE
TO PLEASE NIMENKA.
- OH, NO!
HE MUST BE THE SAGE TOKAJIN.
- THIS HAS BEEN A FINE DAY--
AN UNUSUAL HALF DEMON
AND A YOUNG GIRL,
ALL WITHIN HOURS.
SO BY TOMORROW I SHOULD HAVE
THE FRUIT OF LONGEVITY.
- DID YOU SEE INUYASHA?
ANSWER ME!
INUYASHA'S NOT HURT, IS HE?
YOU'LL BE SORRY IF HE IS.
- LISTEN TO KAGOME CHEW HIM OUT,
NOT A SIGN OF FEAR.
- THAT COMES FROM EXPERIENCE,
I SUPPOSE.
- HELLO! I'M TALKING TO YOU.
UH!
- PIPE DOWN AND GO TO SLEEP.
- [MOANING]
- [GASP] KAGOME!
- NOW MY HANDS ARE FILTHY.
- I CAN'T STAND IT!
HUMAN BODIES ARE SO WEAK
AND VULNERABLE.
I'VE LOST TOO MUCH BLOOD.
I'M STARTING TO GET DIZZY.
- STILL ALIVE, ARE YOU,
HALF DEMON?
- KAGOME'S CLOTHES.
SHE COULDN'T BE!
WHERE'S KAGOME?
TELL ME WHERE THE GIRL IS!
- EXTRACTING NOURISHMENT
HAS BECOME VERY BOTHERSOME
SINCE YOU BROKE MY GOURD.
- EXTRACTING NOURISHMENT?
- WHY THE ANGRY LOOK?
- WHERE'S KAGOME, YOU ANIMAL?!
- OH, I SEE.
YOUR EXPRESSION SAYS IT ALL.
YOU'RE IN LOVE
WITH THAT FILTHY GIRL.
YOU'LL SEE HER SOON ENOUGH...
INSIDE MY BELLY, THAT IS.
YOU WILL BOTH BECOME THE FRUIT
OF LONGEVITY, AND I WILL RELISH
EVERY LAST BITE.
HA HA HA!
- YOU'RE DESPICABLE.
YAAAH! UH!
- YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
YOU CANNOT ESCAPE
FROM THOSE THORNY ROOTS.
- INUYASHA!
- BECAUSE I'M THIS SMALL,
I DON'T KNOW HOW EFFECTIVE
MY WIND TUNNEL WILL BE,
BUT HERE GOES!
AAH!
- KAGOME.
- WAIT, INUYASHA.
- KAGOME IS DOWN
IN THE BASEMENT.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- [MOAN]
WHAT SMELLS SO SWEET IN HERE?
HUH? WHERE AM I?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
- KAGOME!
- INUYASHA!
- UH.
- UM.
- AH!
- SHE'S ALIVE.
- INUYASHA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THESE ARE JUST SCRATCHES.
COVER UP.
IT'S TORN, BUT IT'S
BETTER THAN NOTHING.
- THANK YOU.
- [GROAN]
- INUYASHA!
INUYASHA?
YOU'VE BEEN FIGHTING SO HARD,
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE A HUMAN NOW.
- UH, THIS WOULDN'T BE BAD
TIMING, WOULD IT?
- [GASP]
[SCREAM]
- HA HA! THEY WON'T GET AWAY.
- LOOKS LIKE INUYASHA'S
IN PRETTY BAD SHAPE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
HIS INJURIES LOOK
PRETTY SERIOUS.
WE REALLY SHOULDN'T TRY
TO MOVE HIM.
- I THINK WE CAN GET OUT.
CAN YOU WALK, INUYASHA?
- OUTSIDE? IS IT MORNING YET?
- IT'S PITCH DARK.
YOU'RE PLANNING TO STAY
AND FIGHT?
- YOU KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT.
- YOU CAN'T!
WE HAVE TO KEEP RUNNING
UNTIL YOUR POWERS RETURN!
- I'LL HAVE TO PROTECT
EVERYONE UNTIL DAYBREAK.
- I GUESS WE CAN'T
JUMP FROM HERE.
WELL, WE CAN'T, CAN WE?
PLUS WE HAVE TO GET MOROKU
AND SHIPPO BACK TO THEIR
NORMAL SIZES.
- I'VE GOT A PLAN.
- NO!
- I HAVEN'T TOLD YOU YET!
- YOU'RE GOING TO TELL ME
TO ESCAPE ALONE, RIGHT? NO!
- IS SOMEONE THERE?
- [GASP]
- DID YOU ESCAPE
FROM THE BOX GARDEN?
- WHO ARE YOU, OLD MAN?
- I'M ASHAMED TO ADMIT IT,
BUT I WAS TOKAJIN'S MENTOR.
- SO THEN YOU'RE A SAGE AS WELL?
- WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
HOW COULD YOU LET THAT ANIMAL
BECOME A SAGE?
- INUYASHA!
- OH, IT WAS NOT I
THAT MADE TOKAJIN A SAGE.
IT WAS NIMENKA.
- THE DEMON TREE.
- YES. IT HAPPENED
ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
- I CAN'T STAND THIS TRAINING
DAY IN AND DAY OUT.
THERE HAS GOT TO BE A FASTER WAY
THAN THIS TO BECOME A SAGE.
HMM? WHAT'S THIS?
HUH. WHO CARES?
CAN'T EAT IT.
- AH, A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
THANK YOU.
- WHO SAID THAT?
- I AM NIMENKA.
YOU THERE. DO YOU WISH
FOR A SAGE'S POWER?
- UH-HUH.
- THEN EAT MY HUMAN-FACED FRUIT.
EAT, AND YOU SHALL POSSESS
THE ART OF THE SAGES.
- EXCELLENT.
SWALLOW THE SEEDS, TOO,
AND YOU SHALL HAVE POWER,
A SAGE'S POWER!
- WHEN ONE EATS THE HUMAN-FACED
FRUIT FROM THE DEMON TREE,
ONE BECOMES A SLAVE TO NIMENKA.
TOKAJIN OBEYED THE TREE'S
COMMAND TO TURN ME
INTO FERTILIZER
SO THAT IT WOULD BEAR
THE FRUIT OF LONGEVITY.
- MASTER SAGE, WHO TRANSFORMED
YOU INTO A PLANT?
- THE FRUIT ALONE ISN'T
ENOUGH FOR LONGEVITY.
YOU SEE, THE FRUIT HAS TO BE
SOAKED AND MADE INTO A POTION,
AND ONLY I HAVE KNOWLEDGE
OF THE PROCESS.
- WHICH IS WHY I LET HIM LIVE.
- [FOOTSTEPS]
HA HA HA! WE MEET AGAIN.
SO THIS IS WHERE YOU ESCAPED TO.
- THE POWER OF THE SHARDS
IS INCREASING!
- TOKAJIN IS NO LONGER HUMAN.
YOU MUST SLAY HIM.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M NO LONGER HUMAN.
HUMANS SPEND THEIR MISERABLE
DAYS SLAVING IN THE MUD,
THEN GROW OLD AND DIE.
MY PARENTS BOTH LIVED
AND DIED LIKE THAT.
I REFUSE TO LIVE SUCH
A WEAK, SENSELESS LIFE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU!
YOU'RE NO BETTER THAN THEY WERE!
YOU SACRIFICED OTHERS
JUST SO YOU COULD HAVE
LONGEVITY!
THAT'S NOT STRONG. THAT'S EVIL!
- I AM MORE POWERFUL THAN ANYONE
YOU'VE EVER KNOWN,
AND THAT'S WHY I CAN TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF THE WEAK.
CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND EVEN THAT?
- WATCH OUT! UGH!
- INUYASHA!
- NIMENKA MADE ME STRONG,
AND SINCE I OBTAINED
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
I HAVE BECOME INVINCIBLE.
I SHALL HAVE ETERNAL LIFE
AND TURN MERE WEAKLINGS
LIKE YOU INTO FERTILIZER!
- YOU PIG!
- STOP, KAGOME.
- [GASP]
- INUYASHA, DON'T MOVE.
- HE WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND
YOUR LOGIC.
I'M A HALF DEMON.
I KNOW ONLY TOO WELL
HOW WEAK MORTALS ARE,
AND I UNDERSTAND
HIS DESIRE TO BE STRONG,
BUT THAT'S WHERE
THE SIMILARITIES END,
YOU DISGUSTING EXCUSE
FOR A HUMAN!
- HOW DARE YOU LECTURE ME,
ESPECIALLY IN YOUR CONDITION!
- IT'S EASY.
LET ME DEMONSTRATE!
- I'VE GOT TO GET THE JEWEL
SHARDS BEFORE THEY MELT
INTO HIS BODY.
[GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA!
- [MOANING]
- HUMAN-FACED FRUITS!
- YOU MUST DRINK A MOUTHFUL
OF THAT POTION THERE.
- HUH?
- WHAT POTION?
- TOKAJIN MADE IT.
IT'S AN IMITATION OF THE SECRET
LONGEVITY POTION,
YET IT'S EFFECTIVE ENOUGH
TO HEAL FLESH WOUNDS.
- WOULDN'T DRINKING THAT
MAKE HIM A SLAVE TO NIMENKA?
- NO, AS LONG AS HE DOESN'T
EAT THE FRUIT.
NOW, DRINK UP
IF YOU WISH TO BE SAVED.
- HA HA HA! DRINK IT.
IT COULD BE ENTERTAINING IF YOU
WERE A LITTLE MORE LIVELY.
- FORGET IT. THE TREE OF
HUMAN-FACED FRUITS USES PEOPLE
AS FERTILIZER.
IT'S DISGUSTING.
WHO'D DRINK THIS STUFF
OTHER THAN SOMEONE
AS DESPERATE AS YOU ARE?
- INUYASHA.
- HA HA HA!
HALF DEMON, YOU'LL REGRET
NOT DRINKING THE POTION.
- HA! I DON'T NEED TO DRINK THAT
STUFF BECAUSE I CAN BEAT YOU
SENSELESS WITHOUT ITS HELP.
- WRETCHED FOOL!
- [GRUNTING]
- HA HA HA!
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE ALL TALK
AND NO ACTION.
- DAMN!
- INUYASHA!
HE'S POWERLESS
WITH HIS MORTAL BODY.
- AND WITH MY SIZE,
THE WIND TUNNEL WON'T
DO MUCH GOOD EITHER.
- I'LL SAVE YOU.
- IT'S USELESS. TOKAJIN CAN'T BE
BROUGHT DOWN WITH AN ARROW.
- I'LL DO IT. WATCH.
I'LL AIM FOR THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- A SACRED AURA'S SURROUNDING
THE BOW AND ARROW.
WHO IS THIS GIRL?
- TOKAJIN!
UH!
THE BOW--WHAT HAPPENED?
- HA HA HA! THE BOW AND ARROW
OF A VANQUISHED SOLDIER
CAN NEVER WORK ON ME.
- KAGOME!
I'LL TEACH YOU NOT TO
BE SO CONFIDENT!
- [MOANING]
- WHY, YOU!
- HURRY, GIRL. YOU MUST
SLAY TOKAJIN NOW.
- USE THIS AS MY WAY
OF MAKING AMENDS.
- HUH?
- HE TURNED INTO
A BOW AND ARROW.
- THE OLD SAGE, HE--HE SQUEEZED
OUT HIS LAST OUNCE OF POWER.
- KAGOME!
- [GASP]
- I'LL TEAR YOU LIMB FROM LIMB!
- I CAN SEE THE GLOW
OF THE JEWEL SHARDS
THROUGH HIS BACK.
THANKS FOR SHOWING ME
THE TARGET!
- [GROANING]
- THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH, OLD SAGE.
- YOU WENCH!
- HOW DARE YOU?
- GET DOWN, KAGOME!
- [SCREAMING]
- NO! INUYASHA!
- KAGOME.
- INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
- SERVES YOU RIGHT.
YOUR MORTAL BODY WILL NEVER
SURVIVE THIS FALL.
- MAYBE NOT, BUT AT LEAST
KAGOME'S ALIVE.
- INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
- HUH?
[GROANING]
- NIMENKA, YOU'RE RESCUING ME?
- NO SUCH THING.
I SIMPLY DON'T WANT TO LOSE
PRECIOUS NOURISHMENT.
- WHAT?
[MOANING]
- HA HA HA.
AT LAST.
I AM ABLE TO MOVE.
FREEDOM IS MINE.
I HAVE AMPLE SHARDS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL,
AND I AM ALL POWERFUL!
NOW, HALF DEMON,
BECOME ONE WITH ME.
- DAMN. DAYBREAK AT LAST.
- HA HA HA!
I NEVER EXPECTED TO CAPTURE
A HALF DEMON, AS WELL.
NOTHING CAN STOP ME NOW.
- DON'T BE SO SURE.
- PREPARE TO DIE, TOKAJIN,
OR SHOULD I SAY TREE
OF THE HUMAN-FACED FRUITS?
- HA! JUST TRY
AND SLAY ME, HALF DEMON!
- YOU ASKED FOR IT!
SEE HOW YOU LIKE MY WIND SCAR!
- [SCREAMING]
- ALL RIGHT!
- FINALLY WE'RE BACK
TO NORMAL AGAIN.
- TOKAJIN MUST HAVE DIED,
AND THAT'S WHAT UNDID
HIS SPELL ON US.
THOSE MEN IN THE BOX GARDEN
HAVE PROBABLY
REVERTED BACK, AS WELL.
- YOU THINK TOKAJIN IS DEAD?
- THEN WHAT ABOUT INUYASHA?
- HE CAN'T BE!
- WHEN INUYASHA FELL,
IT WAS STILL DARK OUT.
DAYLIGHT HADN'T BROKEN YET.
I'M AFRAID THERE ISN'T
MUCH HOPE.
- AAH! INUYASHA IS GONE FOREVER!
- DON'T SAY THAT.
INUYASHA IS STILL ALIVE.
- OH, BUT HE WAS SO BADLY HURT,
AND NO MORTAL COULD SURVIVE
A FALL FROM A CLIFF LIKE THIS!
- DON'T CRY, SHIPPO.
LET US PRAY FOR HIS REPOSE.
- OH, MOROKU.
- INUYASHA LEFT BEHIND
NO REGRETS WHEN HE PASSED ON.
HE WANTED TO SAVE YOU,
EVEN IF IT COST HIM HIS LIFE.
- HE DID THAT TO SAVE ME?
HOW CAN I EVER LIVE
WITH THAT ON MY SHOULDERS?
HOW COULD HE BE SO STUPID,
DOING THAT WHILE HE HAD
NO DEMON POWER?
INUYASHA, YOU'RE SUCH AN IDIOT!
STUPID, STUPID!
HOW COULD YOU DIE ON ME?!
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
- YES, HE WAS INDEED FOOLISH.
- YOU SAID IT!
INUYASHA WAS THE BIGGEST
FOOL OF ALL!
- HEY! I'M GONE
FOR ONLY 5 MINUTES,
AND LOOK WHAT HAPPENS
TO ALL OF YOU.
SO, WHO WERE YOU CALLING
AN IDIOT?
- YOU'RE ALIVE, INUYASHA!
YOU'RE ALIVE!
- I KNEW YOU'D SURVIVE
THAT SEEMINGLY FATAL FALL.
NO, REALLY, I DID.
- THANK GOODNESS.
- I AIN'T SO EASY TO KNOCK OFF.
HOW COULD YOU EVEN THINK
ANYTHING SO INCREDIBLY STUPID?
- YOU CAN HARDLY BLAME US.
WE WERE WORRIED ABOUT YOU, OK?
- HUH?
- WE KNEW YOU WERE
OVEREXERTING YOURSELF.
- STOP BLUBBERING! I'M ALIVE,
SO WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
- I'M NOT BLUBBERING!
- OK, THEN, CRYING.
- I AM NOT!
- ARE SO!
- AM NOT!
- ARE!
- NOT!
- ARE SO!
- SHUT UP AND SIT!
- NOW HE'S DEAD!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- OH, SANGO, YOU'VE BEEN
GONE JUST 3 DAYS,
AND YET IT SEEMS
LIKE A LIFETIME.
TWO WOULD-BE APPRENTICES
SHOWED UP AT YOUR VILLAGE,
WANTING YOU TO TEACH THEM
TO BECOME DEMON SLAYERS,
AND THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL SISTERS?
OH, POOR YOU, SANGO.
TOUGH BREAK.
MAYBE I SHOULD GO LEND A HAND.
NEXT TIME, "THE BEAUTIFUL
SISTER APPRENTICES."
ARE YOU OK, SANGO?
COME ON.
IT'S NOT AS IF I HAVEN'T TOUCHED
YOU THERE BEFORE.