>> ♪ KOKORO NO NAKA NO
JIORAMA NO MACHI WA
KIBOU NO HIKARI DE
KIRAMEITE IRU
KAGEROU NO HANE DE
HABATAITA YUME WA
KIMI TO BOKU TO NO SAGASHIMONO
SHINJITSU WA ITSUMO
HITOMI NI HISONDE IRU
AOKU
BOKURA WA DOKO MADE YUKOU
FUTARI NO MIRAI IMA SASURATTE
BOKURA WA TABI O TSUZUKERU
EIEN NO ARIKA
OWARI NAI YUME
KONO TE O HANASAZU
OIKAKETE IKITAI
ZUTTO ♪
[FOOTSTEPS]
>> HOW BEAUTIFUL YOU MUST HAVE
BEEN WHEN YOU WERE ALIVE,
MIDORIKO.
WAS IT THAT BEAUTY THAT GAVE YOU
THE POWER TO CREATE THE SACRED
JEWEL?
>> THE SACRED JEWEL, SAID TO
GIVE POWER TO THE PERSON WHO
POSSESSES IT AND GRANT HIS EVERY
WISH.
OUR JOURNEY BEGAN WITH OUR
SEARCH FOR THE SHARDS OF THE
JEWEL...
AND NOW WE CONTINUE TO HUNT FOR
NARAKU, WHO POSSESSES MOST OF
THE JEWEL SHARDS.
THE BREEZE FEELS SO NICE.
>> IT'S SO PEACEFUL.
>> WE HAVEN'T FOUND A SINGLE
CLUE LEADING TO NARAKU, AND HERE
YOU ARE, WASTING TIME LIKE THIS.
HURRY UP AND EAT.
>> TO MAKE THINGS WORSE, DEMONS
THAT WERE LAYING LOW WHEN NARAKU
WAS AROUND ARE NOW COMING OUT OF
THE WOODWORK IN DROVES.
THINGS COULDN'T GET MORE
DISCOURAGING.
>> YOU GOING SOMEWHERE WITH
THIS?
>> I'M SAYING, LET US RELAX AND
AT LEAST ENJOY OUR MEAL IN
PEACE.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE A LITTLE
SYMPATHY FOR THEM, INUYASHA.
>> WHAT?
>> KAGOME, SANGO, AND MIROKU
AREN'T STRONG LIKE US.
THEY'RE ONLY WEAK MORTALS.
YOU'RE EXPECTING THE IMPOSSIBLE.
>> MMPH.
>> DID HE CALL US WEAK MORTALS?
>> WELL, IT'S A GOOD THING YOU
UNDERSTAND, SHIPPO.
>> HUH? WHAT?
I DIDN'T SAY SOMETHING WEIRD,
DID I?
>> NOPE, NOT AT ALL.
>> AHH.
I'M NOT WRONG, RIGHT?
>> HMM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, STRONG LIKE
US?
GO AHEAD AND KEEP EATING, THEN.
WAKE ME UP WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
>> YOU BETCHA.
>> CLEAN, FRESH AIR AND
DELICIOUS RICE BALLS.
>> AND NICE WEATHER.
>> THAT, TOO.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> WHAT IS IT?
IS SOMETHING WRONG, KAGOME?
>> I THINK I FEEL SOMETHING...
KIND OF LIKE THE SACRED JEWEL,
AND YET NOT EXACTLY.
>> WELL, WHICH ONE IS IT,
KAGOME, YES OR NO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THIS TIME, IT'S DIFFERENT.
>> WHERE IS IT?
>> OVER THAT WAY.
IT'S COMING CLOSER.
>> [PANTING]
>> HUMAN HUNT.
>> HUH?
>> LEAVE HIM TO ME.
>> YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
>> IT'S OK. DON'T WORRY.
>> AH, THANK YOU.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT, HALF-DEMON?
HOW DARE YOU INTERFERE?
>> IS THIS GUY THE ONE?
>> UH-HUH.
I SENSE HE HAS A SACRED JEWEL
SHARD IN HIS BELLY, BUT IT--
>> SO WHERE'D YOU GET THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD?
>> HA HA!
NOW THAT YOU KNOW ABOUT MY
SACRED JEWEL, YOU BETTER DO AS I
SAY AND SURRENDER THE HUMAN.
>> OR YOU COULD SURRENDER THE
JEWEL SHARD AND ESCAPE WITH YOUR
LIFE, IF YOU'RE LUCKY.
>> I DETEST SUCH IMPUDENCE.
YOU WILL REGRET OPPOSING ME.
RAAR!
>> NOTHING BUT HOT AIR.
>> AGH!
THAT WASN'T SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
AGH!
>> HMM. HUH?
>> WHAT'S THAT?
THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> IMPOSSIBLE.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
HUH?
>> OH!
INUYASHA SHATTERED THE JEWEL IN
HIS HAND.
>> HMM. YOU FOOL.
THE SACRED JEWEL DOESN'T SHATTER
THAT EASILY.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, INUYASHA, BUT
HOW COME I SENSED ITS PRESENCE,
THEN?
>> BECAUSE IT'S AN IMITATION OF
THE REAL SACRED JEWEL.
>> HMM?
>> IT WOULD SEEM THAT THERE IS A
DEMON TRYING TO CREATE A
DUPLICATE OF IT.
>> HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> I'LL EXPLAIN, BUT FIRST, MAY
I HAVE A DRINK OF WATER?
>> SURE. HERE.
HAVE SOME OF THIS.
>> MY, HOW REMARKABLE.
SUCH A BEAUTIFUL WATER
CONTAINER.
>> WHAT'S WITH HIM?
>> HMM.
>> MY NAME IS IZUMO.
MY FAMILY HAS SERVED AS GUJI FOR
CENTURIES.
>> GUJI? WHAT'S THAT?
>> BEATS ME.
>> WELL, YOU SEE, "GUJI" IS
ANOTHER WAY TO SAY "SHRINE
KEEPER," LIKE MY GRANDFATHER.
>> INDEED.
SO YOU'RE A PRIESTESS YOURSELF.
>> YOU WERE SAYING?
>> I BEGAN MY STUDIES IN ORDER
TO BETTER SERVE THE GODS, AND AS
MY THIRST FOR KNOWLEDGE GREW, I
TRAVELED TO MANY COUNTRIES TO
LEARN, RESEARCH, AND RECORD.
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT YOU AND
YOUR PERSONAL HISTORY.
TELL US ABOUT THE IMITATION
SACRED JEWEL.
>> THE VERY PURPOSE OF MY
STUDIES IS TO LEARN EVERYTHING I
CAN ABOUT THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> SO THAT'S WHY YOU KNOW ABOUT
ITS EXISTENCE.
>> ALL THE UNIVERSE, EVERYTHING
IN LIFE, IS CREATED FROM 4
SPIRITS.
>> ARAMITAMA, NIGIMITAMA,
KUSHIMITAMA, AND SAKIMITAMA ARE
THE 4.
WHEN THESE 4 SPIRITS ARE IN
SYNTHESIS, THEY BECOME ONE
SPIRIT, OR THE HUMAN HEART.
>> WOULD SOMEBODY ANSWER MY
QUESTION?
>> I HEARD THAT BEFORE, BUT I
NEVER REALLY UNDERSTOOD IT.
>> ME, EITHER.
>> HOW ABOUT YOU START
EXPLAINING THE PART WHERE THAT
DEMON GOT HOLD OF THE FAKE
SACRED JEWEL?
>> SOMEONE GAVE IT TO HIM.
>> WHO DID?
>> IT WAS A DEMON.
>> ARE YOU LOOKING FOR A FIGHT?
>> NO, NOTHING OF THE SORT.
>> STOP IT, INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> SO TELL ME, IZUMO, WHY WAS
THAT DEMON CHASING YOU, ANYWAY?
>> BECAUSE I HAPPENED TO COME
ACROSS SOME DEMONS AND THEIR
FAKE SACRED JEWELS.
>> WHAT?
>> I HEARD THAT THERE WAS A
SHRINE WHICH TOLD THE LEGEND OF
THE SACRED JEWEL, AND I MADE MY
WAY TO THE MOUNTAIN PATH.
EVENTUALLY, THOUGH, I GOT LOST.
THAT'S WHEN I CAME UPON A DEMON
HANDING THE SACRED JEWEL TO THAT
WORM DEMON.
>> WAS THIS DEMON CALLED NARAKU?
>> NO.
HE CALLED HIMSELF ORUCHIDIU, AND
HE SAID THAT THE JEWEL WAS NOT
YET COMPLETE, BUT THAT SOON, A
TRUE SACRED JEWEL WOULD BE MADE.
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
>> SO THAT MEANS A DEMON IS
MAKING SACRED JEWELS?
>> UNFORTUNATELY, THAT IS ALL I
WAS ABLE TO OVERHEAR.
>> STRANGE, I DON'T SENSE THE
PRESENCE OF ANY DEMONS.
>> IT WAS JUST AROUND HERE THAT
I CAME UPON THE DEMON.
>> [SNIFFS]
I'M NOT CATCHING ANY SCENT OF
NARAKU.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE HE'S
INVOLVED IN THIS.
>> HOW ABOUT YOU, KAGOME?
DO YOU SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL?
>> UH-UH. NO, NOT AT ALL.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT WAS REALLY A
STRONG FEELING TO BEGIN WITH.
>> HA! BECAUSE IT'S A FAKE.
>> IT PROBABLY DOESN'T WORK ALL
THAT WELL, EITHER.
>> LOOK!
THERE'S A VILLAGE OVER THERE.
>> NO ONE IS AROUND.
>> THERE'S NO SIGN OF ANYONE.
I WONDER IF SOMETHING HAPPENED
HERE.
>> WAIT.
WHERE DID THE PRIEST GO?
>> HUH?
>> IZUMO.
>> HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> OHH.
>> WELL?
>> WORD HAS IT THAT THIS SHRINE
HOUSES THE DEITY OF ORIGIN.
>> HUH?
IT'S EMPTY.
>> WHAT IS THE DEITY OF ORIGIN?
>> THERE IS A LEGEND THAT CLAIMS
THAT THE SPIRITS KUSHIMITAMA AND
SAKIMITAMA WERE BORN FROM THE
HEART OF THIS DEITY.
>> OH, IS THAT SO?
>> KUSHIMITAMA EMBODIES CHI, OR
KNOWLEDGE, AND SAKIMITAMA
EMBODIES AI, OR LOVE.
>> ARAMITAMA, OR YUU, AND
NIGIMITAMA, OR SHIN--
YUU, SHIN, CHI, AI.
THESE ARE THE 4 SPIRITS THAT
MAKE UP THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> OHH, MY HEAD.
>> LET'S SAVE ALL THIS TALK FOR
LATER.
I'M GETTING A WEIRD FEELING FROM
THIS PLACE, AND I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD INVESTIGATE
A LITTLE MORE AROUND HERE.
>> I'LL CHECK JUST OUTSIDE THE
VILLAGE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HUH, WE HAVEN'T FOUND A THING
YET.
>> OHH.
UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I WONDER HOW IT IS THAT THE
SUN CAN BE SO WARM AND BLINDING.
>> WHO KNOWS?
IT'S JUST ONE OF THOSE NATURAL
THINGS.
>> NATURAL?
NOT TO ME, IT ISN'T.
IS SOMETHING BURNING ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THE SUN, AND WHAT
IS THE DISTANCE FROM US TO THE
SUN?
>> THIS GUY THINKS UP SUCH WEIRD
STUFF.
>> NO.
I'VE NEVER MET A MAN IN THIS ERA
WHO THINKS LIKE HE DOES.
I GOT TO SAY, I'M IMPRESSED.
>> ARE THERE A LOT OF GUYS LIKE
HIM IN YOUR WORLD?
>> HMM.
>> WHY DOES THE NIGHT FALL AT
THE DAY'S END?
>> IZUMO IS TALKING LIKE THAT
BECAUSE HE'S A SCHOLAR.
>> OK.
SAY...
>> YES?
>> THOSE 4 SPIRITS YOU WERE
TALKING ABOUT EARLIER, WHAT DO
THEY MEAN, THE YUU AND CHI?
>> DO YOU MEAN YUU, SHIN, CHI,
AND AI, FOX DEMON?
>> YEAH, THOSE ONES.
>> ARAMITAMA, OR YUU, REPRESENTS
THE SPIRIT OF COURAGE.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
NOW WE'RE GETTING SOMEWHERE WITH
ALL OF THIS.
>> YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> SHIN REPRESENTS FRIENDSHIP.
CHI REPRESENTS KNOWLEDGE, OR
KNOWING THE WAYS OF THE WORLD,
AND AI IS, OF COURSE, LOVE.
>> OK.
THAT STUFF ALL MAKE SENSE.
THAT MITAMA SOMETHING OR OTHER
YOU WERE SAYING WAS STARTING TO
GIVE ME A HEADACHE.
>> ARAMITAMA OF COURAGE,
NIGIMITAMA OF FRIENDSHIP,
KUSHIMITAMA OF KNOWLEDGE,
SAKIMITAMA OF LOVE.
WHEN THESE 4 SPIRITS ARE
GATHERED INTO ONE AND GOOD AND
EVIL ARE SEALED INSIDE THE
CHAOS, THEN IT IS POSSIBLE FOR A
SACRED JEWEL TO BE CREATED.
>> AGH!
OH, NO. THERE HE GOES.
HE'S LOST ME AGAIN.
UHH...
>> STOP! DON'T RUN AWAY!
>> HUH?
>> HEY, I THINK THAT WAS SANGO.
>> [PANTING]
>> I WON'T HURT YOU.
>> STAY AWAY!
NO!
WHAT?
>> WE'RE TRAVELERS, NOT BANDITS
OR MURDERERS.
HAVE NO FEAR.
WE WON'T DO ANYTHING TO HARM
YOU.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, SANGO?
>> HUH!
STAY AWAY, DEMON.
>> HUH?
>> YES.
SHIPPO AND KIRARA ARE INDEED
DEMONS, BUT THEY AREN'T BAD.
WHY? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DID SOMETHING TERRIBLE HAPPEN IN
THIS VILLAGE?
>> [SOBBING]
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE AFRAID.
WHATEVER HAS HAPPENED HERE, WE
PROMISE TO TRY TO PROTECT YOU.
>> THE DEMONS--
THE DEMONS CAME.
>> DID DEMONS ATTACK THIS
VILLAGE?
>> EVERYONE WAS TAKEN AWAY.
I WAS PUNISHED FOR BEING NAUGHTY
AND WAS PUT IN THE CHICKEN COOP.
HA!
HMM?
>> SURRENDER AND COME OUTSIDE.
OTHERWISE, WE'LL BURN YOU ALIVE
IN YOUR HOMES.
>> WAIT! WE'RE COMING.
>> UH! FATHER! MOTHER!
>> EVERY ONE OF YOU MUST COME
OUT.
SEARCH FOR ANYONE WHO MIGHT
STILL BE HIDING.
>> UH!
>> [SOBBING]
EVERYONE WAS TAKEN AWAY BY THE
DEMONS THAT NIGHT.
>> WHEN WAS THIS?
>> ABOUT 5 DAYS AGO.
I'VE BEEN HIDING IN THE COOP
EVERY DAY SINCE THAT TERRIBLE
NIGHT.
>> WELL, THAT ANSWERS THE
QUESTION WHY THE VILLAGE IS
DESERTED.
>> TELL ME, WHAT HAPPENED TO
THEM ALL?
WHY DID THE DEMONS GO AND TAKE
MY PARENTS AWAY?
WHY?
>> HMM.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
DID THE DEMONS EAT THEM?
>> NO.
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT IS THE
CASE.
IF THEY HAD ONLY COME TO EAT,
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE TAKEN THEM
ALL AWAY.
>> IZUMO.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE THEY'VE BEEN
EATEN.
>> HE'S RIGHT.
THE DEMONS THAT DID THIS AREN'T
FOOLS.
THEY KNOW THAT IF THEY ATTACK
THE VILLAGES AND KILL EVERYONE,
PEOPLE WILL HIRE DEMON SLAYERS.
>> IF THE DEMONS TOOK THEM
ALIVE, THEY MUST HAVE A REASON
FOR IT.
>> YOU THINK MY PARENTS ARE
STILL ALIVE, THEN?
>> QUITE LIKELY.
WE'LL GO FIND THEM.
>> AND WE'LL SLAY THE DEMONS,
TOO.
>> I'M SO GLAD.
THANK YOU.
>> HMM.
>> THIS WON'T BE EASY.
IT'LL BE NIGHT SOON, AND I
HOPE WE CAN FIND THEM IN THE
DARK.
>> NIGHTFALL.
HMM.
THE NIGHT CLOAKS ALL IN
DARKNESS.
EVEN THE MOST BEAUTIFUL CREATURE
IN NATURE IS HIDDEN BENEATH ITS
BLACK ROBE.
>> HUH?
UH, YOU TOOK THE WORDS RIGHT OUT
OF MY MOUTH.
>> HUH?
I SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> WHAT A SURPRISE.
I THOUGHT I SENSED THE PRESENCE
OF MORTALS.
I SEE YOU HAVE REAL SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS.
>> HUH! IT'S THEM!
>> HUH?
>> THEY'RE THE ONES WHO
KIDNAPPED MY PARENTS AND THE
OTHERS.
>> SURRENDER NOW AND HAND OVER
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> YOU'RE THE ONES WHO SHOULD BE
SURRENDERING.
SO YOU'RE THE WICKED ORUCHIDIU.
WHERE DID YOU TAKE THE
VILLAGERS?
>> AH, MONK, I'VE HEARD MANY
RUMORS ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONE WITH THE WIND
TUNNEL IN YOUR HAND.
>> YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
GOOD.
THEN YOU'LL KNOW WHAT HIT YOU.
>> TAKE HIM.
[DEMONS GROWLING]
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> AAH!
>> NOW, WILL YOU BEHAVE AND DO
AS WE ASK?
HMM! AAH!
>> SEEMS THIS SACRED JEWEL IS A
CLUSTER OF NOXIOUS DEMONIC
VAPORS...
>> UHH!
>> MIROKU.
>> AND UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
IT'S TOXIC TO HUMANS.
>> IT'S AN EVIL SPIRIT.
THAT JEWEL WILL DEFILE THE HUMAN
SOUL.
>> EVERY ONE OF THESE DEMONS
POSSESSES A FAKE SACRED JEWEL.
[DEMONS LAUGHING]
>> WHY, YOU...
>> HRGH!
>> IZUMO, LISTEN.
TAKE THE BOY WITH YOU AND HIDE
SOMEWHERE.
>> YES, RIGHT AWAY.
>> TAKE THIS, DEMONS.
>> THIS WAY.
>> UH. HUH!
>> [ROARS]
>> UH!
>> HAH!
>> HUH?
>> HIRAIKOTSU! HYAH!
YOU'RE MUCH STRONGER THAN THE
AVERAGE DEMON.
>> COULD THE SACRED JEWEL BE
THAT POWERFUL, EVEN THOUGH IT'S
AN IMITATION?
>> I STILL DON'T GET IT.
HOW DID THEY MAKE A DUPLICATE
SACRED JEWEL?
>> MAYBE WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT IT
AFTER THEY'RE GONE.
[DEMONS GROWLING]
>> NOW, THEN, GIVE IT UP.
YOU'VE NO HOPE.
>> THERE'S NO CHOICE, BUT TO USE
MY WIND TUNNEL AGAIN.
>> YOU CAN'T.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
>> BUT--
>> HMM.
>> RRAGH!
>> HUH?
INUYASHA.
>> IRON REAVER, SOUL STEALER!
>> WHERE WERE YOU?
>> OH, SAVE IT.
HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO KNOW YOU'D
BE ATTACKED?
>> SUCHIGUMO, IKAKU.
>> [GROWLING]
[DING]
>> HUH!
DON'T THINK THAT SWALLOWING A
FAKE JEWEL WILL MAKE YOU STRONG.
UH! HUH?
>> RELEASE US.
>> HA HA HA!
>> IZUMO!
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
>> HAH!
>> OOP!
>> AHA!
>> WIND SCAR!
UH!
>> AAAAAH!
>> OHH.
>> YOU DID IT.
>> NO, I DIDN'T.
THE OTHERS ALL GOT AWAY.
SANGO!
OVER THERE! LET'S GO.
>> AHH, SUCH DELICIOUS-LOOKING
SOULS.
>> DON'T YOU EAT ANY OF THEM,
KAMAGAERU.
HERE. TAKE THIS BOY'S SOUL, TOO.
>> UH!
UH, UH...
HUH?
FATHER! MOTHER!
UH!
>> HA HA HA!
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'LL JOIN THEM SOON ENOUGH.
>> GUEO.
NOW THEN, IT'S TIME FOR US TO
PUT YOUR SKILLS TO THE TEST.
>> ARE YOU SURE IT'S THIS WAY,
INUYASHA?
>> YEAH.
THIS WHOLE PLACE REEKS OF BLOOD
AND DEMONS.
>> SENSING ANYTHING, KAGOME?
>> I THINK IT'S STRAIGHT AHEAD
IN THIS DIRECTION.
I'M NOT ENTIRELY SURE, THOUGH.
THE FEELING ISN'T VERY CLEAR.
>> [ROARS]
>> HUH?
>> I CAN FEEL THE JEWEL COMING
THIS WAY.
[RUMBLING]
>> RRGH.
AAH!
HRRGH. BASTARD.
>> THOSE ARE ALL FAKE SACRED
JEWELS.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> COME ON.
SHOW ME WHAT YOU'VE GOT, YOU
FOOLISH HALF-BREED.
>> SO WHAT IF I'M A HALF-DEMON?
>> RAAGH!
>> HUH?
A TOXIC MIASMA.
>> RRGH!
>> AAH!
>> UH!
>> HAH!
>> DID YOU SEE THAT?
>> WHOA! HE'S SO STRONG.
>> UH!
>> HA!
>> IF THERE'S ONE THING I CAN'T
STAND, IT'S AN UGLY DEMON WITH
ATTITUDE.
>> THE WIND SCAR DIDN'T EVEN
WORK.
>> PRIESTESS WITH THE SACRED
JEWEL.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> THE HUMAN SOUL MUST BE
POLISHED, TOO.
OTHERWISE, THE JEWEL IS NO MORE
THAN A STONE.
>> WHAT'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
>> [GROWLING]
>> AAH!
>> WAAH!
>> ♪ AKAKU NIJIMU
TAIYOU WA SUBETE O
TERASHITE KITA
IMA MO MUKASHI MO
KONO YUUYAMI NI
EGAITERU SOUZOU WA
HATASHITE KONO TE NI
OENAI MONO NA NO KA?
MOTTO IMA IJOU NI
HADAKA NI NATTE
IKITE YUKU JUTSU OSHIETE YO
HONNO SUKOSHI DAKE
WATASHI O YOGOSHITE
SOU YATTE HITORI
KIZUTSUITARI
MAWARI O NAKUSHITA TO SHITE MO
SHINJITSU NO UTA WA
KONO MUNE NI NAGARE
SHINJITSU NO UTA O
MICHISHIRUBE NI SHITE ♪
>> MY MOTHER NAMED ME GUEO.
>> SO YOU'RE THE ONE BEHIND ALL
THIS.
YOU TRICKED US ALL.
>> PRIESTESS, YOUR SOUL AND THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS WILL FORM
THE BASIS OF A REAL SACRED
JEWEL.
I WILL USE THE POWER OF THE
SACRED JEWEL TO FREE MYSELF FROM
THIS DESTINY.
>> NEXT TIME, "THE SACRED JEWEL
MAKER, PART II."
>> I SHALL POSSESS ALL THINGS
BEAUTIFUL IN THIS WORLD.