[THUNDER RUMBLES]
>> [GASPS]
UHH...
WHAT IS THIS?
HUH?
OH, WHO ARE YOU?
AAH!
>> THERE'S BEEN A STRING OF
MURDERS AT THE SURROUNDING
TEMPLES?
>> YES, LATELY A NUMBER OF MONKS
AND PRIESTS OF GREAT SPIRITUAL
STANDING HAVE BEEN KILLED.
>> MONKS AND PRIESTS?
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
>> UNFORTUNATELY, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT ALL MEANS.
>> IT'S A TERRIBLE STORY.
DOES IT HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THE REMAINING SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS?
>> I WOULD HOPE THAT NARAKU
WOULDN'T GO SO FAR AS TO KILL
ORDINARY HUMANS.
>> SO, PROBABLY NOT.
>> THEN I GUESS IT'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH US.
>> BESIDES, THERE ISN'T ANYONE
OF GREAT SPIRITUAL STANDING
AMONG US, ANYWAY.
>> YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN,
SHIPPO.
>> [LAUGHING]
>> COME, COME.
YOU DO ME SUCH GREAT INJUSTICE.
>> MASTER MIROKU!
>> HUH?
>> HEY, THAT'S--
>> IT'S HACHI, THE RACCOON DOG.
>> MASTER MUSHIN IS GOING
TO DIE?
>> YES, IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT I SAW IT MYSELF.
>> MUSHIN IS THE MONK WHO RAISED
YOU, ISN'T HE, MIROKU?
>> MUSHIN.
I REMEMBER, WE WENT TO SEE HIM
TO TREAT YOUR WIND TUNNEL.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, HACHI?
TELL ME EVERYTHING YOU KNOW.
>> YES, OF COURSE, YOU SEE--
FOR THE PAST FEW DAYS I'VE BEEN
STAYING AT MASTER MUSHIN'S
TEMPLE.
>> AAH!
[PANTING]
MASTER MUSHIN!
>> [COUGHING]
IT'S NOTHING.
>> YES, BUT--
OH, MASTER MUSHIN!
>> I TOLD YOU, IT'S NOTHING.
[COUGHING]
>> AND SO, YOU SEE, THAT'S WHY
I RUSHED OVER HERE TO ASK FOR
YOUR HELP.
>> HMM.
IT SEEMS THAT HACHI WAS NOT
EXAGGERATING.
>> MIROKU!
>> IT'S BEEN A RATHER LONG
WHILE, HASN'T IT, MASTER MUSHIN?
>> HMM.
>> MASTER, IS SOMETHING
THE MATTER?
>> MIROKU, DEATH WILL COME TO
YOU TONIGHT.
JUST KIDDING.
>> I SHOULD THINK THIS IS NO
TIME FOR YOU TO BE JOKING
LIKE THIS.
>> HMM?
>> PLEASE TELL ME, MASTER,
DID HACHI SPEAK THE TRUTH?
>> HACHI?
>> HACHI SAID THAT YOU WERE
GOING TO DIE SOON.
>> UHH, IT'S NOT A LIE, I FEAR
I AM GOING TO DIE VERY SOON.
[COUGHING]
UHH.
IT SEEMS TO BE THE FATE THAT HAS
BEEN CHOSEN FOR ME.
I MAKE NO COMPLAINTS, BUT I'M
GLAD THAT I GET TO SEE YOU ONE
MORE TIME.
>> [SNORES]
[SQUEAKS]
>> LOOK, WE'RE ALL GONNA DIE
EVENTUALLY SO THERE'S NO SENSE
GETTING ALL SENTIMENTAL
ABOUT IT.
>> INUYASHA!
>> NO, ACTUALLY, INUYASHA
IS RIGHT.
EVENTUALLY ALL LIVING THINGS
DIE.
>> MIROKU, EVEN IF THAT'S TRUE,
THERE MUST BE SOME WAY WE CAN
MAKE IT EASIER FOR HIM.
>> [SIGHS]
>> MASTER?
MASTER!
MASTER MUSHIN!
>> OH, OH, GOODNESS, I GUESS
I DOZED OFF FOR A BIT.
>> UH, IS MASTER MUSHIN REALLY
GOING TO DIE?
>> UMM, MASTER MUSHIN, TELL ME,
IS THERE ANYTHING AT ALL YOU'D
LIKE TO DO?
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> SHE MEANS YOU BETTER TAKE
CARE OF ANY UNFINISHED BUSINESS
BEFORE YOU GO TO THE OTHER
WORLD.
>> INUYASHA!
>> AH, WHAT?
>> SIT, BOY!
>> OH!
>> WELL, HOW ABOUT IT, MASTER?
>> HMM, MAYBE DRINK SOME SAKE.
>> YOU'RE ALREADY DRINKING SAKE.
>> WELL, THAT'S COVERED.
SO, FIRST YOU CAN CLEAN THE
TEMPLE TOP TO BOTTOM FOR ME.
>> FIRST?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HOW THE HECK DID I GET ROPED
INTO DOING ALL THE DUSTING!
>> GREAT JOB, KEEP UP THE GOOD
WORK.
>> REMEMBER, IT'S HIS LAST WISH.
>> PHEW, CLEANING THIS HUGE
TEMPLE SURE IS A BIG JOB.
>> HMM, YOU'RE RIGHT.
MIROKU'S WIND TUNNEL.
IF HE COULD USE THE WIND TUNNEL,
THEN...
>> WIND TUNNEL!
CHECK IT OUT!
THE DIRT ON THE FLOOR, THE MESS
IN THE BEDROOMS--WITH MY
HANDY DANDY PATENTED WIND TUNNEL
YOU DON'T NEED TO USE A SILLY
OLD BROOM ANYMORE!
SEE, SPIC-AND-SPAN IN NO TIME
FLAT.
>> THE SUCTION POWER IS SUPER
STRONG.
>> GOTTA HAND IT TO THE HUMAN
VACUUM CLEANER.
>> [LAUGHING]
>> WOW, IT'S EVERY HOUSEWIFE'S
DREAM.
>> MUST BE ALL THE DUST.
>> AHH, FINISHED ALREADY?
NEXT YOU CAN AIR OUT ALL
THE BEDDINGS.
>> AAH!
TETSUSAIGA!
>> HEY, HEY, NOT SO HARD,
INUYASHA.
>> HUH!
>> HE'S PRETTY DETERMINED.
>> YEAH, WELL, THERE'S NO FOE
INUYASHA WON'T TACKLE.
>> NEXT, CUT THE GRASS.
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
YAH!
>> AND NOW, THE LAUNDRY.
>> AND GO!
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> WELL, LOOKS LIKE THAT'S IT.
>> MM-HMM!
>> WE CLEANED THE ENTIRE TEMPLE,
AIRED OUT ALL OF THE BEDDING,
AND WE DID ALL THE LAUNDRY
AS WELL.
THAT MEANS...
>> LET'S GO PREPARE DINNER.
>> YEP!
LET'S DO IT.
>> THERE'LL BE NO NEED FOR THAT.
>> LOOKS EXPENSIVE.
>> OF COURSE IT'S EXPENSIVE.
IT'S ONE OF THE FINEST INNS
IN THE COUNTRY.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO EAT AND
DRINK TO MY HEART'S CONTENT
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
>> LISTEN HERE, YOU GLUTTONOUS
MONK.
YOU HAD BETTER BE DYING LIKE YOU
SAY YOU ARE, YOU GOT IT?
>> OF COURSE, WOULD I ASK FOR
ALL OF THESE THINGS IF I WEREN'T
ACTUALLY DYING?
NOW, COME ON, LET'S GO!
>> THAT OLD GEEZER.
>> NOW, COME ON, MIROKU.
>> IT IS HIS LAST WISH.
>> HA HA HA.
VERY CLASSY.
OOH, YES, AREN'T YOU PRETTY.
>> [LAUGHING]
>> NOW, THERE, THERE.
REMEMBER, IT'S HIS LAST WISH.
>> HUH.
>> CLEANING, WASHING, AND THEN
A FEAST.
NOTHING TOO OUTRAGEOUS ABOUT
THOSE REQUESTS.
>> YEAH, WELL HE'S PROBABLY TOO
DRUNK TO THINK OF ANYTHING ELSE.
>> THE WANTS AND DESIRES OF A
RURAL MONK ARE RATHER SIMPLE
IT WOULD SEEM.
>> TELL US, MASTER MUSHIN,
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE YOU WANT
TO DO?
>> AHH, WELL TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I WOULD LIKE TO DRINK SOME SAKE.
>> YOU'RE ALREADY DRINKING SAKE!
>> YOU MISUNDERSTAND.
THE SAKE I DESIRE IS NO ORDINARY
SAKE.
>> HUH?
>> WELL THEN WHAT KIND OF SAKE
IS IT?
>> HMM, A LEGENDARY SAKE.
THE MIST OF SAGES.
>> MIST OF SAGES?
>> 4 MOUNTAINS AWAY FROM HERE,
THERE IS A SACRED PEAK KNOWN AS
KASUMEDAKE.
LEGEND HAS IT THAT THE SAGES WHO
LIVE THERE MAKE A VERY RARE
SAKE, KNOWN AS THE MIST OF
SAGES.
THOSE WHO DRINK THIS SAKE FEEL
AS THOUGH THEY HAVE ASCENDED
TO HEAVEN.
ITS TASTE IS INDESCRIBABLY
DELICIOUS.
>> OH, SO YOU WANT US TO ACQUIRE
SOME OF THIS FABLED SAKE
FOR YOU?
>> HOLD ON, I HAVE NOT FINISHED
THE STORY YET.
MANY HAVE SET OUT TO ACQUIRE
THE MIST OF SAGES, BUT NOT ONE
OF THESE INTREPID CONNOISSEURS
OF THE DRINK HAS EVER RETURNED
WITH IT.
IF I COULD ONLY DRINK THIS SAKE,
I WOULD HAVE NO REGRETS LEAVING
THIS WORLD.
>> I GUESS WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
>> HUH?
>> HEY, HOLD ON, MIROKU.
>> YOU MEAN YOU'D GO FOR ME?
>> I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU BE ABLE
TO LEAVE THIS WORLD WITHOUT
ANY REGRETS.
>> MM...HMM.
>> WELL, WELL, MIROKU.
AREN'T YOU MR. COMPASSIONATE.
>> SO ARE YOU, INUYASHA,
FOR AGREEING TO COME ALONG AND
HELP ME.
>> ANYTHING TO STOP THE OLD GUY
WHINING.
>> HMM.
>> HUH?
HEY, MIROKU, LOOK UP AHEAD.
IS THAT?
>> KASUMEDAKE.
THE MOUNTAIN MASTER MUSHIN TOLD
US ABOUT.
NOW WE JUST HAVE TO FIND THIS
MYSTERIOUS SAGE AND CONVINCE HIM
TO PART WITH SOME OF HIS
PRECIOUS SAKE.
>> SOUNDS PRETTY EASY, AS LONG
AS HE'S WILLING TO SHARE IT.
>> HUH?
>> HEY, MIROKU--
>> I KNOW, I SENSE IT, TOO.
THIS IS NO SAGE, THIS IS THE
AURA OF A DEMON.
>> UHH, UHH...
>> WHAT IS THIS?
THE MIST!
>> THIS MIST, WHAT IS IT?
>> LISTEN UP, BE READY FOR
ANYTHING, OK?
>> HMM.
>> [GROWLING]
>> HI, I'M KAGOME, AND I'D LIKE
TO SING FOR YOU!
>> WHAT IN THE--
>> LA LA LA, THIS IS ME--
>> THIS KAGOME WOULD LIKE TO
DANCE FOR YOU!
>> AND THE THIRD KAGOME WOULD
LIKE TO LAUGH LIKE AN IDIOT.
HA HA HA!
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT'S
GOING ON AROUND HERE.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, IT LOOKS LIKE
THERE ARE 3 OF ME.
OH, WELL, TIME TO SING!
I'M SO HAPPY, LOOK AT ME!
>> I'M KAGOME, LOOK AT ME!
>> SOMEBODY, PLEASE KILL ME NOW.
>> EVERYBODY LISTEN TO ME,
DON'T INHALE THE MIST!
THIS IS THE WORK OF THE DEMON,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS MIST IS
EXACTLY, BUT IT MAKES YOU
INTOXICATED, SO DO NOT INHALE
IT, NO MATTER WHAT!
>> THINK YOU'RE A LITTLE LATE
THERE, MIROKU, THEY'RE ALREADY
THREE SHEETS TO THE WIND.
>> WELL I WAS REFERRING TO
THE REST OF US, OF COURSE.
>> ALL RIGHT, TIME FOR ANOTHER
SONG!
>> YEAH!
>> HEY, GIVE IT A REST,
YOU THREE!
>> HA HA HA.
>> HMM?
>> HA HA, OHH.
>> SANGO?
>> UHH, AHH.
>> UHH--AAH--
>> INUYASHA.
>> SANGO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> FORGET ABOUT THE OTHERS,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
>> WHATCHA TALKIN' ABOUT?
>> OH, I'M SO SICK OF THAT
TWO-TIMING MONK, AND 3 KAGOME'S
ARE DEFINITELY A CROWD.
COME ON, LET'S LEAVE THEM.
LET'S GO AND DEFEAT NARAKU.
OK?
>> UHH...
>> NO!
>> SIT, BOY!
SIT, SIT, SIT, SIT, SIT!
>> [SOBBING]
>> LOOK, NOW THE POOR GIRL'S
CRYING.
>> NO, SANGO--
>> UH-OH, THE TWO-TIMING MONK
IS GONNA TRY TO CONSOLE HER.
NOT A GOOD IDEA.
>> MIROKU, WHY YOU FLIRTING
CHEAT!
>> UHH.
>> NOW SHE'LL TEACH HIM
A LESSON.
>> GO, GO!
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
UH!
>> UHH!
UH, IS THIS THE DEMON'S PLAN?
TO INTOXICATE US WITH HIS
DEMONIC POWER AND MAKE US FIGHT
EACH OTHER?
INUYASHA, TRY TO SCATTER THIS
MIST WITH YOUR WIND SCAR!
>> I'M--A--LITTLE--BUSY--
RIGHT--NOW!
>> OH, RIGHT.
OHH.
OH, WELL.
I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I MUSTN'T FEAR BEING POISONED
BY THIS MIST.
THIS IS FOR YOU, MASTER MUSHIN.
AND...WIND TUNNEL!
UHH!
HMM?
>> HUH?
>> ARE YOU THE SAKE SAGES?
HUH?
HMM.
>> OHH, LOOKS LIKE IT'S
ALL GONE.
HMM.
>> OUT OF SAKE ALREADY?
>> HMM?
>> HERE.
THERE YOU GO.
SO, TELL ME, HOW DOES IT TASTE?
>> SUPERB.
MMM.
HMM, MIROKU?
>> HMM?
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HMM.
MASTER, IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE
SINCE WE SAT AND TALKED LIKE
THIS, HASN'T IT?
>> YES.
>> FATHER!
FATHER!
UHH!
LET ME GO, MUSHIN!
>> YOU WILL BE PULLED INTO YOUR
FATHER'S WIND TUNNEL, TOO,
IF YOU GO.
>> FATHER!
NO!
>> DOES IT BOTHER YOU?
>> HUH?
>> I SUPPOSE THAT MY IMMINENT
DEATH WOULD BOTHER YOU EVEN IF
I TELL YOU NOT TO LET IT.
>> I SUPPOSE IT WOULD.
>> NARAKU IS STILL ALIVE,
ISN'T HE?
>> YES.
>> THE UNCERTAINTY OF TOMORROW
CAN ONLY BE UNDERSTOOD BY THOSE
WHO DON'T KNOW FOR SURE IF THEY
WILL LIVE ANOTHER DAY.
UNTIL NARAKU IS DEFEATED, YOU
WILL NOT BE ABLE TO FORGET ANY
OF YOUR TRAGIC MEMORIES.
EVEN WHEN YOU ARE DRUNK,
AS I AM.
>> THAT'S NOT ENTIRELY TRUE,
MASTER.
WHILE I MAY NOT BE ABLE TO
FORGET, I CAN ALLOW MYSELF
TO BECOME INTOXICATED WITH THE
HOPE OF DEFEATING NARAKU.
MASTER?
DID YOU HEAR ME?
NO!
MASTER MUSHIN, MASTER MUSHIN,
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME!
MASTER MUSHIN!
NOO!
[SOBBING]
>> [SNORES]
>> HUH?
HMM?
WAIT, DON'T TELL ME HE'S
NOT DEAD.
>> [SNORES]
>> WHAT!
>> OH, MAN, YOU HAVE GOT TO BE
KIDDING ME.
>> I MOST ASSUREDLY AM NOT
KIDDING YOU.
>> SO, BECAUSE ALL THOSE MONKS
AND PRIESTS OF GREAT SPIRITUAL
STANDING WERE BEING MURDERED,
YOU FIGURED YOU WERE GOING TO BE
MURDERED AS WELL?
>> EXACTLY, MY DEAR.
>> SO THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
YOUR HEALTH?
>> I'M AS STRONG AS A HORSE.
WHY, I CAN FIGHT MY WEIGHT
IN WILDCATS!
>> THEN WHAT ABOUT THE BLOOD
HACHI SAW YOU SPIT UP?
>> THE BLOOD?
OH, A SMALL FISH BONE GOT STUCK
IN MY THROAT, THAT'S ALL.
>> OH!
>> UH, I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
>> HA HA.
>> OH, MAN, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
>> WHO ELSE AROUND HERE IS SO
DEVOUT AND HIGHLY SPIRITUAL?
THE ANSWER IS OBVIOUS, THE NEXT
VICTIM IS SURE TO BE--
>> BELIEVE US, YOU'RE NOT IN ANY
DANGER!
>> WELL, I COULD BE IN THE
RUNNING AT LEAST.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
>> LIKE I SAID, WE'RE ALL GONNA
DIE SOMEDAY, SO WHY WORRY?
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK YOU MAY
BE RIGHT.
MY HEAD STILL HURTS.
>> I THINK IT WORKED OUT FINE.
>> HUH?
>> HOW DO YOU FIGURE?
>> WELL, I--I JUST THOUGHT THAT
A LITTLE KINDNESS NEVER HURTS,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> WE NEED TO BE ON OUR WAY NOW,
MASTER.
>> YES.
HMM.
>> [LAUGHS]
>> JUST WHAT IS THIS CREEPY KID
UP TO ANYWAY?
HALF KILLING SO MANY IMPORTANT
MONKS AND PRIESTS, HE MUST BE
PEERING INTO THEIR HEARTS
OR SOMETHING.
>> KAGURA, I'M DONE WITH THIS
ONE, DISPOSE OF HIM FOR ME.
I COULDN'T FIND ANYTHING.
EVEN IF THEY'RE HIGHLY
SPIRITUAL, THEY'RE STILL MERELY
HUMANS.
>> WHAT EXACTLY IS IT YOU WERE
TRYING TO FIND?
>> THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT.
THAT'S WHERE THE FINAL SHARD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL LIES.
>> [SNORES]
>> A MYSTERIOUS INCIDENT THAT
KEEPS HAPPENING AT NIGHT.
>> THE HOUSES OF THE WEALTHY ARE
TARGETED, REGARDLESS OF HOW WELL
PROTECTED THEY ARE.
>> SOMEONE BREAKS IN AND STEALS
THEIR VALUABLES.
>> IT'S NO ORDINARY BANDIT FROM
THE LOOKS OF IT.
>> A DEMON THAT CAN TURN ITSELF
INVISIBLE, I WONDER IF WE CAN
DEAL WITH IT WORKING WITH THAT
OLD EXORCIST WOMAN?
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA," A STRANGE
INVISIBLE DEMON APPEARS.
>> JUST LEAVE EVERYTHING TO ME,
I'LL SOLVE THIS MYSTERY
FOR SURE.