>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSAIGA.
>> THE REMAINING BAND OF 7 ARE
REUNITED WITH BANKOTSU,
THE STRONGEST OF THE 7.
HIS HUGE HALBERD AND INUYASHA'S
TETSAIGA ARE ABOUT TO CLASH.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE, "INUYASHA."
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> I ASSUME YOU'RE THE BAND OF
7.
>> WELL, WELL, WELL.
SO THE WOLF GETS HERE BEFORE THE
DOG, I SEE.
>> I'LL KILL YOU!
[GRUNTING]
NICE TRY.
HUH?
>> AAH!
HEH!
>> YAH!
>> QUIT JUMPING AROUND!
>> MOVE, YOU WIMPY WOLF!
WELL, WELL.
FOUND YOU.
>> HMM.
[GASP]
>> INUYASHA!
>> SHUT UP.
SO, YOU'RE INUYASHA.
MY, MY, AREN'T YOU A STRONG ONE?
>> I SUPPOSE YOU MUST BE THE
LAST OF THE BAND OF 7.
>> YEAH.
I'M THE LEADER, BANKOTSU.
>> SO, WHAT SORTS OF COWARDS
GANG UP ON A PATHETIC LITTLE
WOLF LIKE THAT?
>> HEY, MUTT!
WHO ARE YOU CALLING PATHETIC?
>> SHUT UP!
I'M NOT THE IDIOT WHO ALMOST GOT
THE JEWEL SHARDS CUT OUT OF MY
LEGS, NOW, AM I?
>> HEY, I WAS DOING FINE BY
MYSELF!
>> INUYASHA.
>> KOGA!
>> HEY.
>> YOU GUYS ARE LATE.
>> SO, YOU'VE ALL ARRIVED.
ABOUT TIME.
>> YOU BASTARDS!
YOU'VE BEEN CAUSING TROUBLE
AROUND HERE LONG ENOUGH.
I'M GONNA SEND EACH ONE OF YOU
BACK TO YOUR GRAVE.
>> SAME HERE.
I'M GOING TO AVENGE THE DEATHS
OF OUR BROTHERS MUKOTSU AND
KYOKOTSU.
>> IT SEEMS AS IF THE ONE WITH
THE LARGE HALBERD IS THE LEADER
OF THE BAND OF 7.
>> YES, ALTHOUGH HE ALSO LOOKS
LIKE THE YOUNGEST.
>> HMM.
HUH?
[GASP]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAGOME?
>> BE VERY CAREFUL, INUYASHA.
THE LEADER--HE HAS 3 SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS IN HIS NECK.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> HMM.
THEY BELONG TO MUKOTSU AND
KYOKOTSU.
>> HUH!
I KIND OF WONDERED WHY YOU WERE
SO FEISTY.
SO THAT'S THE EXPLANATION.
>> THEN THAT MUST MEAN NARAKU
GAVE BANKOTSU THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS.
>> HUH?
>> HMM!
>> MAYBE.
>> REVIVING A BUNCH OF NO-GOOD,
LOWLIFE MURDERERS LIKE YOU?
THAT DOES SOUND LIKE NARAKU.
>> YEAH, AND HE TOLD US TO USE
THE POWER OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
SHARDS TO KILL EVERY LAST ONE OF
YOU.
>> HEH!
>> YAH!
>> I'M GONNA TEAR YOU APART!
>> THINK SO?
JUST TRY IT!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
>> IT'S A DEADLOCK.
>> INUYASHA.
>> WELL, DON'T JUST SIT THERE,
GINKOTSU.
>> AARGH!
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME!
>> ARE YOU OK?
>> KAGOME?
KAGOME!
>> A WORD OF ADVICE, INUYASHA.
YOU SHOULD REALLY BE LOOKING
AFTER YOURSELF!
YAH!
>> ARE YOU OK, KAGOME?
>> YES, THANKS.
>> GOOD.
SHE'S SAFE.
HEY THERE, KOGA.
THANKS A LOT FOR PROTECTING
KAGOME.
>> SHUT UP!
I DIDN'T DO IT FOR YOU, OK?
>> THANK YOU FOR RESCUING ME,
KOGA.
>> I WANT YOU TO GO AND HIDE
SOMEWHERE.
THESE GUYS ARE AFTER THE SHIKON
SHARDS IN MY LEGS.
>> YES, BUT I--HUH?
THAT'S RENKOTSU.
HE'S THE ONE WHO STOLE THE JEWEL
SHARDS FROM ME, AND HE STILL HAS
THEM!
>> I UNDERSTAND NOW.
THAT GIRL CAN SEE THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS.
GRR!
>> YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
>> YAH!
>> IF BANKOTSU FINDS OUT THAT I
DIDN'T TELL HIM ABOUT THE JEWEL
SHARDS, THERE'LL BE HELL TO PAY.
GINKOTSU, AIM FOR THAT GIRL.
>> YES.
>> WHAT?
KAGOME, NO!
>> RUN AWAY QUICKLY, KAGOME!
>> HURRY AND KILL HER.
>> OVER MY DEAD BODY, YOU WILL!
>> KOGA!
>> UNH!
>> AAH!
>> WHAT?
>> YOU CAN'T TOUCH ME!
>> GOOD.
HE'S AWAY FROM THE CANNON.
>> WE'VE GOT TO GET THE JEWEL
SHARDS BACK.
>> WAIT. WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> THAT GUY TOOK MY SHIKON JEWEL
SHARDS.
>> DO IT, MIROKU!
>> I'M ON IT.
AAH!
>> I WON'T LET YOU GO ANY
FURTHER.
>> SUIKOTSU!
>> I'VE DECIDED THAT YOU ARE
GONNA FIGHT ME.
TO BE HONEST, I CAN'T STAND
DOCTORS OR MONKS!
>> BUT YOU YOURSELF WERE A
DOCTOR.
>> GREAT.
LEFT OUT AGAIN.
EVERYONE AROUND HERE IS JUST SO
SELFISH.
SO IS THIS ALL THAT'S LEFT
FOR ME?
>> WHY DON'T YOU COME OVER HERE
AND SAY THAT?
>> I'VE GOT TO SAY, IT'S JUST NO
FUN FIGHTING A WOMAN.
>> GRR.
>> SO HURRY UP AND DIE,
WILL YOU?
>> NO SUCH LUCK!
>> GRR!
>> I SUPPOSE BEING A HALF-DEMON,
YOU SHOULD BE STRONGER THAN A
HUMAN.
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
NARAKU COULDN'T BEAT YOU.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> YOU DON'T SEEM ALL THAT TOUGH
TO ME!
>> DAMN IT!
IF YOU KNOW WHERE NARAKU IS,
THEN TELL ME NOW.
>> I REALLY DON'T LIKE TO BE
QUESTIONED!
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW
NARAKU'S WHEREABOUTS...
ASK MY BLADE.
[GRUNT]
>> WOW!
IT'S SUCH A LARGE MOUNTAIN,
ISN'T IT, MASTER JAKEN?
>> I FEEL AWFUL.
WHY DID I HAVE TO COME TO A
WRETCHED PLACE LIKE THIS ONE?
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, MASTER
JAKEN?
>> I'M IN PAIN!
>> HOW COME?
>> DON'T YOU GET IT?
MOUNT HAKUREI IS SACRED.
DEMONS LIKE ME HAVE A DIFFICULT
TIME EVEN APPROACHING IT.
YOU PROBABLY DON'T FEEL
ANYTHING, RIN, BECAUSE YOU'RE AN
INNOCENT HUMAN GIRL, BUT I FEEL
AS IF I'M BEING DRAGGED--
HEY, HEY! WAIT!
>> COME ON.
LET'S GO LOOK JUST A LITTLE
FURTHER, MASTER JAKEN.
>> SHE DIDN'T EVEN LISTEN TO A
WORD I SAID.
[SPUTTERING]
HEY, HEY!
NO, WAIT!
I MUSTN'T--
STOP! I GOT TO GO BACK!
NO!
>> HUH?
>> OHH.
OHH, THERE'S NO WAY A MASSIVE
EVIL LIKE NARAKU COULD EXIST
HERE.
SO THEN WHY WOULD LORD
SESSHOMARU WANT TO...
>> THE SACRED BARRIER.
HMM.
I CAN GO NO FURTHER.
I CAME HERE FOLLOWING THE SCENT
OF NARAKU'S SERVANT, THE BOY,
KOHAKU.
BUT ALL OF A SUDDEN, THE SCENT
STOPPED, LIKE IT WAS CUT OFF.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, WHERE ARE
YOU?
>> GOT TO GET AWAY.
>> I WONDER WHERE HE COULD HAVE
GONE.
>> HELP ME.
>> HMM?
HUH?
KOHAKU?
THERE'S NO MISTAKE!
IT'S KOHAKU!
>> OHH.
HUH? WHA?
HEY, RIN, DON'T GO OFF ON YOUR
OWN!
LORD SESSHOMARU WILL HAVE MY
HIDE IF HE FINDS OUT I LET--AAH!
I WAS SO DANGEROUSLY CLOSE TO
BEING PURIFIED.
AAH! OH!
OH, GREAT, SHE'S GONE!
OHH!
>> KOHAKU!
KOHAKU!
>> HMM?
HUH?
IT'S YOU!
>> I AM SO GLAD.
I--I GET TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> RIN, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> WE DIDN'T PART ON GOOD TERMS
LAST TIME, AND IT KIND OF
BOTHERED ME.
>> GO BACK!
THIS IS NO PLACE FOR SOMEONE
LIKE YOU.
SHH!
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> BE QUIET, RIN.
>> OHH.
>> GO BACK SLOWLY, BEFORE THEY
NOTICE THAT YOU'RE HERE.
>> KOHAKU.
>> HURRY UP AND LEAVE.
IF THEY SEE YOU, THEY'LL KILL
YOU.
>> YES, OK.
BUT WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO YOU?
>> DON'T WORRY.
THEY WON'T ATTACK ME.
NOW GO!
>> UH-HUH.
KOHAKU.
>> DIE, MONK!
>> NOT IF I CAN HELP IT!
>> MIROKU!
>> PAY ATTENTION!
>> HMM?
>> AAH!
>> I'LL ROAST YOU ALIVE WITH THE
FIRES FROM HELL ITSELF!
>> THAT KIND OF STUFF WON'T WORK
ON ME.
>> YES!
>> HUH?
>> NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS!
>> THE SAIMYOUSHOU.
>> NOT RETREAT!
>> WHAT?
HAS SOMETHING HAPPENED?
>> DON'T DISTURB ME.
I WANT TO DEAL WITH INUYASHA
FIRST.
APPARENTLY I NEED TO WRAP THINGS
UP QUICKLY.
SO YOU'D BETTER SAY YOUR
PRAYERS, INUYASHA!
>> HA!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'D BETTER
START PRAYING.
NOW TASTE MY WIND SCAR!
BYE, BYE, BANKOTSU.
>> SO THIS IS THE WIND SCAR.
>> AH!
>> HUH?
>> OH, NO, BANKOTSU!
>> HE DID IT!
>> HA!
WELL, HE SURE HAD IT COMING.
HUH?
>> DAMN.
YOU PUT A SCAR ON MY BANRYU.
>> HUH?
>> GOOD JOB, GINKOTSU.
YOU SAVED ME.
ALL RIGHT!
ALL RIGHT, ALREADY!
INUYASHA, THAT'S ALL I HAVE TIME
FOR TODAY.
>> YOU HAVE GOT TO BE KIDDING
ME.
>> OK, BREAK TIME'S OVER.
DAMN IT!
>> I MUST GET RID OF HER...
>> KAGOME!
>> BEFORE SHE GIVES ME AWAY.
FIRE!
>> AAH!
>> WHAT?
>> OH, NO!
>> RENKOTSU, YOU WON'T GET AWAY.
HMM.
HUH?
OHH!
>> I'VE GOT YOU.
>> WELL, THIS IS INCONVENIENT.
HE SAYS HE NEEDS US TO RETURN
IMMEDIATELY, IF NOT SOONER.
SEE YOU!
>> WHY, YOU.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU GET AWAY!
HUH?
[LAUGHTER]
>> INUYASHA, IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
>> IT'S NARAKU!
>> I'M SO SORRY.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME, LORD
SESSHOMARU.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
RIN RAN OFF BEFORE I COULD STOP
HER.
[SOBBING]
>> WHERE IS SHE?
INSIDE THE BARRIER?
>> AAH!
YOU MUSTN'T GO IN THERE, MASTER!
IF YOU ENTER SACRED GROUNDS,
EVEN YOU'LL BE INSTANTLY
PURIFIED!
>> BE QUIET AND LOOK BEHIND YOU.
>> HUH?
IS THAT RIN?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> KOHAKU WAS THERE, WASN'T HE?
>> HUH?
>> UH, NOW BE HONEST, RIN.
YOU CAN'T DECEIVE MASTER'S KEEN
NOSE.
>> DOES LORD SESSHOMARU ACTUALLY
INTEND TO KILL KOHAKU?
UH, THE TRUTH IS, KOHAKU HELPED
ME ESCAPE.
THERE WERE LOTS AND LOTS OF
DEMONS IN THE CAVE.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
DEMONS?
>> KOHAKU PROTECTED ME FROM THE
DEMONS.
SO, UM...
>> DEMONS BEHIND THE SACRED
BARRIER?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU?
>> NOW I UNDERSTAND.
NARAKU'S LITTLE TRICK.
>> HA HA HA!
WELL, I MUST GIVE YOU CREDIT FOR
COMING THIS FAR.
>> WHY, YOU!
>> INUYASHA, I DON'T THINK
IT'S ACTUALLY HIM.
>> YEAH.
IT'S ONE OF HIS DEMON PUPPETS.
>> BUYING TIME FOR THE BAND OF 7
TO ESCAPE, ARE YOU?
>> HA HA HA!
>> HUH?
WHAT IS THIS?
SANGO, THAT'S A PUPPET, RIGHT?
>> YES.
IT HAS TO BE A DECOY THAT NARAKU
CREATED.
>> WHY DO YOU ASK THAT, KAGOME?
>> THIS DEMON PUPPET IS
DIFFERENT FROM THE OTHERS HE'S
USED.
>> I HAVEN'T GOT TIME FOR FAKES!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, KOGA?
>> HA HA HA!
I WON'T LET YOU PASS.
>> WHOA!
HE'S GIGANTIC!
>> STAND BACK.
BE CAREFUL.
>> UNH!
HAH!
>> TIME TO USE MY WIND SCAR!
>> HUH?
>> I WON'T LET YOU PASS.
>> YOU TRYING TO GET AHEAD OF
US, KOGA?
>> SHUT UP, MUTT!
AN INCOMPETENT HALF-BREED LIKE
YOU WOULD ONLY LET THE BAND OF 7
GET AWAY!
THEY CAN'T HAVE GONE FAR YET,
AND THEY WON'T GET AWAY FROM ME.
>> HEY! HOLD ON A SECOND!
>> WAIT, INUYASHA.
>> HMM?
>> SO YOU NOTICED IT, TOO,
KAGOME?
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE
ABOUT THIS DEMON PUPPET.
IT SEEMS CLEAN.
>> HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, NARAKU'S
PUPPET SEEMS CLEAN?
>> IT SEEMS PURE, LIKE THE
BARRIER AROUND MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> MOUNT HAKUREI?
>> HEY!
IT SMELLS--IT SMELLS NICE.
>> IT SMELLS OF--
OF WATER AND FLOWERS.
>> WATER AND FLOWERS?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> HMM?
>> BUT WHY WOULD NARAKU'S DEMON
PUPPET SMELL LIKE THIS?
>> WHERE ARE YOU?
WHERE'D YOU GO?
UNH!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
IT'S SOME KIND OF BARRIER.
>> WE CAN SEE IT NOW,
BANKOTSU--MOUNT HAKUREI.
JEEZ!
WHAT'S WITH THIS AIR?
IT MADE ME SICK THE LAST TIME WE
CAME HERE, TOO.
>> IT SEEMS TO EXTEND FURTHER
NOW.
>> I SUSPECT THE SACRED BARRIER
HAS BEEN STRENGTHENED.
THIS WAY, NEITHER INUYASHA NOR
KOGA CAN COME AFTER US.
>> BUT IT'LL BE TOUGH FOR US,
TOO, EVEN THOUGH WE ARE HUMAN.
>> YES.
>> WAIT!
IT SEEMS WE WON'T HAVE TO GO ALL
THE WAY TO THE BASE OF THE
MOUNTAIN.
>> BANKOSTU, SIR.
>> HI, KOHAKU.
SO WHO'S THIS ALBINO CHILD?
>> SHE'S KANNA.
>> WHAT'S THIS?
HUH?
HEY!
HIM AGAIN?
>> WHAT, DO YOU KNOW HIM?
>> THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
HE'S THE ONE WHO KILLED MUKOTSU.
>> IT'S INUYASHA'S OLDER
BROTHER, SESSHOMARU.
>> AH, SO HE WAS INUYASHA'S
OLDER BROTHER.
>> YES, I SEE.
SO WHAT?
>> YOU ARE TO FIND HIM AND KILL
HIM, TOO.
>> HEY!
YOU'D BETTER NOT TELL ME YOU
DRAGGED US ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
JUST TO TELL US THAT.
WE WERE IN THE MIDDLE OF
DESTROYING INUYASHA.
>> IF YOU HAD CONTINUED
FIGHTING, YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
KILLED.
>> WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT, KID?
>> YOUR HALBERD CANNOT DEFEAT
INUYASHA'S TETSAIGA.
>> HMM!
WHAT, YOU MEAN BECAUSE OF
THIS MEASLY SCRATCH ON BANRYU?
WHY, IT HARDLY EVEN--HUH?
>> IT CAN BECOME MUCH STRONGER.
>> HUH?
>> YES.
>> OHH.
NOW I GET IT.
HEY, RENKOTSU, TIME TO HAND THEM
OVER, RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I KNEW ALL ALONG THAT YOU
TOOK SHIKON JEWEL SHARDS FROM
THAT GIRL KAGOME AND HID THEM
FROM ME.
IF YOU PREFER, I COULD CUT THEM
OUT OF YOUR NECK.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
>> PLEASE DON'T BE ANGRY, BIG
BROTHER.
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO GIVE THEM
TO YOU ALL ALONG.
>> AHH.
THAT'S A WISE DECISION,
RENKOTSU.
YOU ARE SMART, AFTER ALL, IT
SEEMS.
HOWEVER, DO NOT MAKE ANY MORE
MISTAKES.
>> UNDERSTOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
NOW, SUIKOTSU...
>> YEAH?
>> AND JAKOTSU, I WANT YOU TO GO
AND TAKE CARE OF THIS
SESSHOMARU.
[GRUNTS]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
SESSHOMARU NOT YOUR TYPE?
>> I KEEP TELLING YOU,
INUYASHA'S THE ONE I WANT!
>> SORRY TO BREAK IT TO YOU, BUT
I DON'T THINK THE FEELING'S
MUTUAL.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF INUYASHA.
[SIGH]
NOW, THEN.
YEAH!
THIS IS GREAT.
>> I KNOW WHICH DIRECTION
INUYASHA IS COMING FROM.
>> NINJAS SURE ARE CLEVER,
AREN'T THEY?
>> I AM NOT A NINJA.
>> HUH?
DAMN HALF-DEMON,
GET READY TO MEET YOUR DOOM.
>> LOOK FOR WATER?
DO YOU MEAN LIKE RIVERS AND
MARSHES AND SUCH?
>> YEP.
WE KEEP LOOKING UNTIL WE FIND
THE SAME KIND OF WATER AND THE
SAME SMELL OF FLOWER.
>> IT WAS THE FIRST TIME I'D
SMELLED A FLOWER QUITE LIKE
THAT!
>> WHAT ABOUT THE BAND OF 7,
INUYASHA?
>> IF WE KEEP FOLLOWING NARAKU,
THEY'RE BOUND TO SHOW UP
EVENTUALLY.
NARAKU, WE WILL FIND YOU.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> MOUNT HAKUREI'S BARRIER HAS
BECOME EVEN STRONGER.
>> NARAKU'S DEMON PUPPET LEFT US
WITH A CLUE: THE SCENT OF WATER
AND FLOWERS.
BUT WHERE WILL IT LEAD US?
>> HIJIRI ISLAND, A SACRED
PLACE.
IT'S SAID THAT A CENTURY AGO, AN
ILLUSTRIOUS MONK BECAME A LIVING
BUDDHA AND IS ENSHRINED HERE.
>> SOMETHING'S BOTHERING ME.
LET'S GO.
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA":
"AFLOAT ON THE LAKE SURFACE:
THE BARRIER OF HIJIRI ISLAND."
>> WHY CAN'T I USE MY WIND SCAR?