>> NARAKU HAS DISPELLED
THE BARRIER AROUND HIS CASTLE.
THIS SINGLE ACT MADE IT CLEAR
THAT HE HAS ABANDONED HIS CASTLE
AND HID HIMSELF ELSEWHERE.
IN THE PAST, NO MATTER WHERE
HE HID, I WAS ABLE TO SENSE
THE PRESENCE OF HIS BARRIER.
BUT NOW THERE IS ABSOLUTELY
NO SIGN OF NARAKU.
IT'S ALMOST AS THOUGH
HE HAS COMPLETELY VANISHED
FROM THIS LAND.
THERE IS SOMETHING MORE TO THIS.
I HAVE HAD MY SOUL COLLECTORS
SEARCH FOR NARAKU'S DEMONIC
AURA, BUT THEY CANNOT DETECT
EVEN THE SLIGHTEST PRESENCE
OF A BARRIER.
HOW COULD HE HIDE A DEMONIC AURA
OF SUCH MAGNITUDE?
[RAIN FALLING]
[THUNDER]
>> WAIT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE REST SOMEWHERE?
>> NOT AGAIN!
WE JUST STOPPED TO REST
A WHILE AGO.
>> I KNOW,
BUT IT STARTED RAINING.
>> ARE YOU A WOMAN OR A CAT?
THIS LITTLE DRIZZLE
DOESN'T EVEN COUNT AS RAIN.
>> OK, BUT THAT'S ONLY
PART OF THE PROBLEM.
>> WHO ARE YOU TO COMPLAIN,
ANYWAY?
YOU'VE GOT IT EASY, RIDING THAT
WEIRD CONTRAPTION OF YOURS.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW
WHY I NEED TO STOP?
BECAUSE MY BUTT'S
GONNA FALL OFF!
OH!
NOW LOOK WHAT YOU MADE ME GO
AND SAY!
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?
>> INUYASHA, ARE YOU READY TO
TAKE THE BLAME IF KAGOME'S
BOTTOM GETS DEFORMED?
>> THAT'S ENOUGH, SHIPPO.
>> HUH. GUESS I'M OUTNUMBERED.
BUT THE SECOND KAGOME'S BUTT
RETURNS TO NORMAL, WE'RE HITTING
THE ROAD AGAIN.
YOU GOT THAT?
>> INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
>> SIT!
>> UHH!
[GROANING]
>> LOOKS LIKE THERE'S GONNA BE
A DOWNPOUR.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'D BETTER HURRY AND TRY
AND FIND SOME SHELTER.
>> [GROANS]
DON'T JUST LEAVE ME.
TRAITORS!
>> AN EVIL DEMON?
>> YES, PRIESTESS.
SEVERAL VILLAGERS HAVE ALREADY
BEEN KILLED BY IT.
>> PRIESTESS, HELP US
AND PUT A SPELL ON THE DEMON.
>> PLEASE.
>> WE BEG YOU.
>> LOOK YONDER.
THE DEMON LIVES IN THE
MISTY SWAMP AT THE TOP
OF THE MOUNTAIN.
>> PRIESTESS, HAVE IT
IN YOUR HEART TO ASSIST US.
>> I'LL HELP YOU.
I'LL GO TO THE MISTY SWAMP.
THIS MUST BE THE PLACE.
I CAN SENSE AN UNCOMMON AIR
ABOUT THIS SWAMP.
>> [GROWLING]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> WHAT?
UH...
>> [GROWLING]
>> [THINKING] HE ISN'T HERE,
EITHER.
I HAVE WANDERED THE COUNTRYSIDE
LOOKING FOR A TRACE OF
THE DEMONIC AURA.
BUT SO FAR, I HAVE NOT COME
ACROSS ANY SIGN OF NARAKU.
WITH NARAKU'S DISAPPEARANCE,
A GROWING NUMBER OF DEMONS
HAS BEGUN TO EMERGE.
SIMPLY TRACKING HIS DEMONIC AURA
WILL NOT HELP ME CAPTURE NARAKU.
>> HALT!
>> [THINKING] A HUMAN.
HE HAS A SERIOUS ILLNESS,
AND HE DOESN'T HAVE LONG
TO LIVE.
>> THE VILLAGERS SURELY GAVE YOU
A HEFTY SUM FOR SLAYING
THAT DEMON.
>> HEFTY SUM?
HA HA! NO SUCH THING.
>> I DON'T CARE
HOW MUCH YOU HAVE.
JUST DROP YOUR LOOT OVER THERE.
>> I DO NOT CARRY ANY MONEY.
>> THERE'S NO TEMPLE OR SHRINE
AROUND HERE FOR YOU TO LODGE.
WHAT FOOL WOULD TRAVEL WITHOUT
CARRYING EVEN A SMALL SUM?
>> IF YOU THINK I LIE,
GO AHEAD AND SEARCH ME.
>> WHAT DO YOU SURVIVE ON, THEN?
MIST?
>> HA HA!
YES, IN A MANNER OF SPEAKING.
>> OH!
[GROANING]
NEVER MIND. OFF WITH YOU.
WHY DO YOU STARE?
LEAVE ME AT ONCE.
>> HMM.
A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> AAH!
>> THAT JEWEL SHARD IS THE ONLY
THING THAT KEEPS YOU FROM DEATH.
ISN'T THAT THE CASE?
>> I'LL BE 70 YEARS OLD
NEXT YEAR.
[COUGHING]
THE AVERAGE MAN LIVES 50 YEARS.
I'VE ALREADY OVERSTAYED
MY WELCOME.
I CAN'T DIE YET, THOUGH,
AND I SHALL HOLD ON AS LONG AS
I HAVE THIS SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
[COUGHING]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN ACCOMPLISH
IN SUCH POOR CONDITION?
>> I CAN FIND MY DEATHBED.
[COUGHING]
>> HMM.
DRINK THIS.
IT SHOULD EASE YOUR PAIN
SOMEWHAT.
>> WHY DO YOU HELP
A MAN LIKE ME?
>> I WISH TO HEAR
THE END OF YOUR STORY.
>> OH.
AHEM.
>> [SNARLING]
>> WHEN WE MET, I WAS LOOKING
FOR A SUITABLE PLACE TO DIE
IN PEACE.
>> I DON'T FOLLOW.
A SUITABLE PLACE?
>> AYE, PRIESTESS.
I'VE COMMITTED ALL MANNER
OF WICKED CRIMES IN THE DAYS
OF MY YOUTH.
MAD KILLER KANSKE--
THAT'S WHAT THEY CALLED ME,
AND RIGHTLY SO.
I KILLED, STOLE,
BURNED DOWN HOUSES.
I DID WHATEVER I PLEASED.
THE WAY I SAW IT, I WOULD LIKELY
BE SLAIN AT A YOUNG AGE, SO I
TOOK WHAT I WANTED AND THOUGHT
NOTHING OF THE CONSEQUENCES.
SOMEHOW I MANAGED TO ESCAPE
DEATH ALL THESE YEARS.
HERE I AM AN OLD MAN,
AND STILL I HAVE NOT DIED.
HUH?
>> IS SOMETHING WRONG?
>> OH.
GROWING OLD IS CRUEL.
THE MEMORY PLAYS TRICKS.
THESE DAYS, I KEEP FORGETTING
THINGS I NEED TO RECALL
AND RECALLING MEMORIES
THAT ARE OF NO USE TO ANYONE.
IT STRUCK ME,
WHEN I FIRST LAID EYES ON YOU,
YOU LOOK REMARKABLY SIMILAR.
>> SIMILAR TO...
>> LONG AGO, I CAME UPON
A PRIESTESS WHO COULD HAVE
PASSED AS YOUR SISTER.
WHAT WAS HER NAME, NOW?
AH, YES.
I BELIEVE IT WAS KIKYO.
>> AH.
PURE COINCIDENCE, I'M SURE.
>> YES, OF COURSE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT 50 YEARS AGO.
IF SHE WERE STILL ALIVE,
SHE'D BE AN OLD WOMAN.
>> YES, IF SHE HAD LIVED.
>> I HEARD THROUGH THE GRAPEVINE
THAT SHE HAD PASSED ON AND THAT
THE JEWEL WAS BURIED WITH HER
IN HER GRAVE.
I CAN'T BEGIN TO IMAGINE
WHERE THIS SACRED JEWEL FRAGMENT
CAME FROM, BUT AT THE VERY LAST
MOMENT, IT FELL INTO MY HANDS.
>> WERE YOU AFTER
THE SACRED JEWEL 50 YEARS AGO?
>> YES--MYSELF AND ANOTHER
FELLOW NAMED ONIGUMO.
>> ONIGUMO?
>> AYE.
HE HAD A BURN SCAR ON HIS BACK
THAT WAS SHAPED LIKE A SPIDER.
I'VE DONE COUNTLESS EVIL DEEDS
IN MY LIFETIME, BUT ONIGUMO WAS
A TRUE VILLAIN.
[LAUGHTER
AND INDISTINCT CHATTER]
AHH.
SO, THE JEWEL WILL GRANT ME
ANY WISH, YOU SAY?
>> ANYTHING AT ALL.
>> WHERE IS IT?
TELL ME, HOW DO I GET MY HANDS
ON THIS SACRED JEWEL?
>> IN THE VILLAGE OVER YONDER,
A PRIESTESS NAMED KIKYO
IS IN POSSESSION OF IT.
>> BRILLIANT!
WE'LL STAGE A SURPRISE ATTACK
ON THE VILLAGE TOMORROW.
>> NO, RESATSU.
I THINK IT BEST IF YOU GO ALONE.
>> WHY IS THAT?
>> KIKYO HAS KEEN SENSES.
IF WE GO IN GREAT NUMBERS,
SHE'LL SURELY ESCAPE US.
>> HA!
AND WHAT COURSE OF ACTION
SHALL I TAKE?
>> WITH YOUR BOW AND ARROW,
YOU CAN EASILY STRIKE HER FROM
A DISTANCE WITH A SINGLE SHOT.
ISN'T THAT SO?
>> OF COURSE.
>> HA HA!
THEN WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR,
RESATSU?
>> HA HA HA!
WHATEVER I WANT, HUH?
I'LL HAVE ALL THE RICE WINE
I DESIRE.
AHH.
AND I'LL TAKE THE WORLD
FOR MY OWN ENJOYMENT.
I'VE FOUND YOU.
DIE, PRIESTESS!
>> [GRUNTS]
>> WHO'S THAT?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> AAH! UHH!
WHO ARE YOU? WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> WHAT'S THIS?
YOU'RE JUST A HUMAN.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU'VE GOT SOME NERVE,
YOU PATHETIC HUMAN, TRYING TO
CUT KIKYO'S LIFE SHORT.
ARE YOU AFTER THE SACRED JEWEL?
>> THAT'S IT.
I'VE HEARD ENOUGH FROM YOU,
DEMON!
HUH?
AAH!
>> YOU'RE JUST LUCKY
I'M NOT A FULL DEMON.
NOW, PREPARE TO DIE.
>> INUYASHA?
>> HUH? OH.
COUNT YOURSELF LUCKY THIS TIME.
>> DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
UP THERE?
>> HUH.
NOTHING I COULDN'T HANDLE.
>> I'M CONFIDENT YOU WOULDN'T DO
ANYTHING VIOLENT WHILE I'M IN
YOUR PRESENCE.
>> UHH!
HUH.
>> [GROANING]
HUH?
WHERE ARE THEY ALL?
WHERE DID MY MEN GET TO?
I WAS DUPED. DAMN THAT ONIGUMO.
HE PLANNED TO STEAL MY MEN AWAY
FROM THE VERY START.
AH, THEY'RE HERE!
[GROWLING]
>> [WOMEN SCREAMING]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [WOMEN SCREAM]
>> RESATSU, YOU'RE BACK!
>> YOU'RE--YOU'RE STILL ALIVE!
>> [GRUNTS]
>> RESATSU, IT'S YOU!
WE DIDN'T MEAN
TO BETRAY YOU, CHIEF.
>> SILENCE!
I'LL SPARE YOUR LIVES IF YOU
COME BACK AND SERVE UNDER ME.
WHERE IS HE?
I'LL FIND YOU, ONIGUMO.
CURSE YOU TO HELL,
YOU DEVIOUS SWINDLER.
I'LL GET MY VENGEANCE!
>> RESATSU, DIDN'T THAT
HALF-DEMON KILL YOU?
>> I LOST MY EYE, THANKS TO YOU.
HOW DARE YOU SET ME UP
LIKE THAT?
[GRUNTS]
>> [WOMEN WHIMPERING]
>> NOW I'LL RETURN THE FAVOR!
>> RESATSU!
>> [GRUNTS]
BURN IN HELL, ONIGUMO!
UHH!
>> WHOA! LOOK AT THAT!
>> HA HA HA HA!
HA HA! BURN. BURN!
BURN HIM TO HELL!
[LAUGHING]
>> [GROANING]
>> RESATSU.
>> HUH.
STUBBORN FIEND REFUSES TO DIE.
THIS PLACE IS GOOD.
YOU MEN, THROW HIM OVER.
>> YES, CHIEF.
>> ONIGUMO,
THIS TIME YOU GO AFTER IT.
>> [BOTH GRUNT]
>> GO FIND THE SACRED JEWEL!
SAY HELLO TO KIKYO FOR ME!
>> SO YOU THREW HIM OVER?
>> AYE, TO THE INFERNAL ABYSS.
>> [THINKING] AND INTO MY HANDS.
HOW IRONIC.
AND THEN WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED AFTER YOU THREW
HIM OVER?
>> THAT WAS THE END.
I STOLE THIS SACRED JEWEL
FRAGMENT RECENTLY FROM
A DYING DEMON I CAME ACROSS.
BUT FOR SOME REASON, IT WON'T
GRANT MY WISHES AS I'D HOPED.
IT PROLONGS MY LIFE
AND NOTHING MORE
AND TEMPTS ONE DEMON AFTER
ANOTHER TO COME AFTER ME.
CURSE THAT WRETCHED ONIGUMO.
EVEN IN DEATH, HE CONTINUES
TO BETRAY ME.
THIS FRAGMENT DOES HELP TO
WARD OFF THOSE DEMONS AS WELL.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> SOMETHING APPROACHES.
MOST LIKELY IT'S COME TO GET
THAT JEWEL FRAGMENT OF YOURS.
>> IS IT A DEMON?
>> WAIT.
I KNOW THAT DEMONIC AURA.
[THINKING] NARAKU.
NO, IT'S NOT. IT'S DIFFERENT.
>> [ROARING]
>> AAH!
>> GIVE IT TO ME!
GIVE ME THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> [ROARING]
>> [GASPING]
WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU TO NARAKU?
>> NARAKU--THAT CURSED WRETCH!
NARAKU SEVERED ME FROM HIM.
HE LEFT ME LOOKING LIKE THIS.
>> [THINKING] IT'S PART OF
NARAKU'S BODY--PART THAT
HE ABANDONED.
>> I NEED A SACRED JEWEL SHARD!
WITH A FRAGMENT, I'LL BE ABLE
TO FIND MYSELF A REAL BODY!
NOW SURRENDER THE JEWEL!
>> UHH!
DAMN YOU, WORTHLESS DEMON.
DIE!
>> AAH! HOW DARE YOU, HUMAN?
>> [SCREAMING]
>> THROW IT TO ME.
THROW THE BOW AND ARROW!
>> HAND OVER THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD!
>> IF YOUR DESIRE FOR IT
IS THAT GREAT...
>> [GASP]
>> HMM.
HYAH!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> THAT ARROW.
>> ARE YOU INJURED, OLD MAN?
>> HOW PITIFUL--
BEING SAVED BY A WOMAN.
YOU'RE NO ORDINARY WOMAN,
I MUST SAY, PRIESTESS.
>> I RETRIEVED IT FOR YOU.
>> I HAVE NO NEED FOR THAT
ANY LONGER.
PLEASE, YOU TAKE IT.
IN RETURN, I WISH YOU
TO GRANT ME JUST ONE REQUEST.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> YOU SEE, I'VE LIVED
A SELFISH LIFE TILL NOW,
BUT THESE LAST YEARS OF AGE
AND SICKNESS HAVE CHANGED ME.
I'VE BECOME AFRAID TO FALL
INTO THE DEPTHS OF HELL.
>> YOU WISH TO BE SAVED?
>> I HEARD OF A SPECIAL PLACE
WHERE EVEN VILLAINS LIKE ME
CAN FIND SALVATION.
AND I'VE TRAVELED IN SEARCH OF
THIS PLACE, BUT I DON'T SUPPOSE
I'LL EVER FIND IT NOW.
>> SO, WHAT NOW?
>> [GRUNTING]
TAKE THIS.
TAKE THIS LOCK OF HAIR
AND BURY IT.
BURY IT SO I MIGHT BE SAVED.
WOMAN, YOU NEVER DID TELL ME
YOUR NAME.
>> IT'S KIKYO.
>> AH.
A BAD JOKE FOR A DYING MAN.
>> THE WHEEL OF DESTINY
IS EVER IN MOTION; ETERNAL.
>> [SNORING]
>> AHCHOO!
>> HMM?
>> AHCHOO! AHCHOO!
>> PUT THIS ON SO YOU WON'T
CATCH A COLD.
>> THANKS.
AHCHOO!
>> NOPE, TOO LATE.
YOU'VE ALREADY CAUGHT ONE.
>> NO.
SOMEONE'S PROBABLY JUST
GOSSIPING ABOUT ME.
AHCHOO!
HUH?
>> DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
WHO'D EVER GOSSIP ABOUT YOU?
HMM. WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
YOU DON'T HAVE A FEVER.
>> THANKS, INUYASHA.
THANKS FOR LOOKING AFTER ME.
>> UH, YOU'RE STARTING
TO GET WARM.
>> HA HA! IT'S OK. DON'T WORRY.
>> UM...
HMM.
>> OH.
YOU CAME ALL THIS WAY
WITH HIS REMAINS?
>> SEEMS TO BE A LOT OF TROUBLE
YOU WENT TO.
>> IT WAS HIS DYING WISH,
AND I GAVE HIM MY WORD.
>> I'VE HEARD ABOUT THIS PLACE
OF PURIFICATION YOU MENTIONED.
I BELIEVE THE MONK'S NAME WAS
HAKUSHIN, IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN.
WASN'T IT?
>> YES, THAT WAS IT.
THERE WAS A TEMPLE STARTED
BY THIS MONK HAKUSHIN, AND IF
THE REMAINS ARE BROUGHT THERE,
HE CAN CLEANSE ANY SIN.
>> WHERE CAN I FIND THIS TEMPLE?
>> IT'S ON MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> MOUNT HAKUREI?
>> BEYOND THIS FOREST,
YOU'LL FIND A VALLEY OVER WHICH
MOUNT HAKUREI LOOMS.
>> SO, THAT MUST BE
THE MOUNTAIN.
SOMETHING FEELS STRANGE.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ALL THE FIELDS HAVE BEEN
RUINED.
YOU'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING,
INUYASHA.
>> I'M NO DOG GOD.
>> COME ON.
WHAT'S SO HARD ABOUT CATCHING
A COUPLE OF MONKEYS?
>> HOW COME I GOT TO DO IT?
>> THERE THEY ARE.
HEY, THEY'RE CUTE.
HERE, LITTLE GUYS.
WANT SOMETHING TO EAT?
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
THOSE BABY MONKEYS HAVE PUT
SOME KIND OF SPELL ON ME!
>> NEXT TIME, "THE THREE SPRITES
OF THE MONKEY GOD."
>> STOP IT, MIROKU.
DON'T USE YOUR WIND TUNNEL!