[PANTING]
- MILORD, HERE IT IS!
THE TOMB THAT WE'VE
BEEN SEARCHING FOR!
- YOU'RE SURE?
- AYE, MILORD.
THE STAFF, AS ALWAYS,
HAS LED US WITHOUT FAIL.
CLEARLY, IT MUST
MEAN THIS TOMB.
ALLOW ME TO PROVE IT.
[SNARLING]
THIS ISN'T RIGHT AT ALL.
MILORD! SUCCESS!
IT IS EXACTLY AS I EXPECTED.
[WHIMPERING]
N-N-N-NICE DOGGIES.
[SNARLING AND BARKING]
- THE FANG.
IT IS A FANG I SEEK HERE.
ONCE I POSSESS IT,
I SHALL TRANSFORM MYSELF
INTO A FAR GREATER POWER.
[SNARLING]
HUH. YET WHY MUST I EXPLAIN?
MY POWER IS WHAT IT IS.
I SHALL NOT ALWAYS
BE LIMITED THUS.
CAN IT BE THAT I AM AFRAID?
OR IS IT MERELY
I KNOW NOT MY OWN LIMITS?
PERHAPS I PRESUME.
[SNARLING]
FANG.
IT IS A FANG I SEEK HERE.
[HOWLING]
POSITION THE STAFF, JAKEN.
- YES, MILORD.
[GIGGLING]
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
- THIS TIME, IT IS
THE BEAUTY WHO RESPONDS.
DO NOT TELL ME
WE HAVE BEEN MISLED.
MILORD! WAIT FOR ME!
YOUR HUMBLE SERVANT COMES!
MILORD!
[PANTING]
- AND HERE I'D THOUGHT
I'D SEEN IT ALL.
WHOEVER HE IS,
LORD INUYASHA WILL WANT TO KNOW.
I'D BEST GO QUICKLY.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- WE REJOIN THE MAIN FORCE
ON THE MORROW.
LET US EAT
OF THIS WAR TONIGHT
SO THAT WE MAY HAVE
STRENGTH FOR BATTLE.
- AYE, AND LET US
GIVE THANKS
THAT WE HAVE SUCH
A LEADER TO FOLLOW.
- LEAD US TO VICTORY!
- THAT I WILL,
AND MORE BESIDES!
[LAUGHTER]
[SHOUTING AND GARGLING]
- WHAT'S THIS?
ARE YE MAD?
- I NEED A BOAT.
- YOU NEED A WHAT?
HA HA HA HA!
BEFORE A BATTLE?
AND WE'RE TO GIVE IT, ARE WE?
- WHY, YES, YOU ARE...
AND NOW.
- I THINK NOT!
OH! AAH!
[GAGGING]
[GASPING]
- WH-WHY, YOU!
- UH, LORD SESSHOMARU,
I REGRET TO INFORM
THERE ARE NO BOATS.
UH...UNLESS YOU COUNT
THOSE OVER THERE, OF COURSE.
- WH-WHAT IS THAT?
- YOU'RE NOT EVEN HUMAN!
- THEY'RE BEASTS.
WORSE THAN BEASTS!
- KILL THEM!
- JAKEN...
I LEAVE THEM TO YOU.
[SNICKERING]
[SHOUTING]
[LAUGHING]
- AND FEEL THE POWER
OF THE STAFF OF THE SKULLS!
- AAH!
[SNICKERS]
THEY MIGHT HAVE BEEN SPARED,
YET SUCH IS THE ARROGANCE
OF THESE LOFTY SAMURAI WARRIORS,
THAT EACH AND EVERY TIME,
LORD SESSHOMARU MUST TEACH THEM
THEIR LESSON ANEW!
HELLO?
LORD SESSHOMARU?
I'VE DONE AS YOU ASKED.
MILORD?
ARE YOU THERE?
WAIT FOR ME, MY LORD!
I'M COMING!
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
WHAT IS THIS?
THE STAFF'S
CHANGED POSITION.
IT MUST BE THE FANG!
IT'S CHANGED LOCATION!
LORD SESSHOMARU?
- YES.
- MIGHTN'T WE ASK...LORD...
INUYASHA WHERE THE TOMB IS?
- INUYASHA!
- AAH!
[GARGLING]
- I PREFER NOT TO THINK OF HIM.
[SPUTTERING]
- FORGIVE ME.
- HE IS,
FOR OUR PURPOSES, DEAD.
WASN'T HE SEALED
TO A TREE 50 YEARS AGO?
- B-B-BUT, SIRE!
THE SPELL!
THEY SAY IT WAS REMOVED
BUT RECENTLY.
[SPUTTERING]
- BESIDES, THE STAFF--
IT'S BEEN ACTING STRANGE.
IT'S BECAUSE OF INUYASHA.
I'M SURE OF IT!
SPEAKING OF THE STAFF, MILORD,
MIGHTN'T YOU REMOVE IT?
I CAN'T BREATHE!
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
[SIGHS]
MADE IT.
SO HOW IS IT I WOUND UP
IN SOME WEIRD, FEUDAL,
ALTERNATE VERSION OF JAPAN?
IN THE PRESENT, MY FAMILY ARE
CARETAKERS OF AN ANCIENT SHRINE.
WITH A THOUSAND-YEAR-OLD TREE
AND A SCARY, SECRET WELL
IN THE GROUNDS,
I GUESS WE'RE KIND OF
WEIRD OURSELVES.
IT WAS THROUGH THE WELL
THAT I MADE IT HERE,
WHERE MONSTERS CAME AFTER
A JEWEL IN MY BODY,
THOUGH I DIDN'T KNOW IT
AT THE TIME.
WITH THE OLD PRIESTESS KAEDE AND
THE VILLAGERS LOOKING AFTER ME,
I'M DOING OK,
THOUGH I DON'T DARE THINK ABOUT
WHAT OTHER MONSTERS MIGHT COME.
- KAGOME, LET'S GO.
- HUH?
- WHAT?
- YOU NEVER SAID MY NAME BEFORE.
- YEAH? WHAT OF IT?
- IT'S JUST THAT I THINK
YOU LIKE ME MORE NOW IS ALL.
- PSSH! DON'T GET EXCITED.
I STILL THINK
YOU'RE PRETTY USELESS.
- REMIND ME NEXT TIME
NOT TO SAVE YOU!
[GROANING]
IF IT HURT SO MUCH,
YOU SHOULD HAVE SAID SOMETHING.
- UGH...LEAVE ME ALONE!
- HE'S RUDE, HE'S CRUDE,
AND SAYS HE HATES ME,
BUT IF WE CAN FIND THE JEWEL,
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS, RIGHT?
- 3 DAYS I'VE BEEN
WALKING NONSTOP.
I THINK I NEED TO REST.
[SIGHS]
[BELL RINGS]
- THAT SOUND--
WHAT'S MAKING IT?
AAH! UGH! UGH!
- HMM. FELT LIKE
I RAN OVER SOMETHING.
MUST HAVE IMAGINED IT.
- FIRST AID TREATMENT?
I DON'T NEED IT.
GO AWAY!
- YOU DO, TOO.
I WAS THERE, REMEMBER?
COME DOWN HERE!
- NOTHING DOING.
- I SAID COME HERE.
- PSSH!
- SIT, BOY.
[GRUNTS]
- WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?
- I'LL JUST TAKE A LOOK, OK?
WHEN YOU'RE HURT THAT BAD,
YOU NEED TO HAVE MEDICAL
TREATMENT, YOU KNOW.
- I SAID GO AWAY!
YOU ACT LIKE
I'M THE ONE WHO LOST!
- LADY KAEDE,
ARE YOU ALL BETTER?
- AYE, CHILD.
ALMOST ALL BETTER.
- AND YOU'RE GOING TO FIND ALL
THE JEWEL PIECES SOON, HUH?
[CHUCKLING]
- NOT SOON PERHAPS, BUT AYE.
IT WOULD HELP IF INUYASHA
AND YOUNG KAGOME
COULD TRY AND LIKE
EACH OTHER A LITTLE MORE.
- THEY DO LIKE EACH OTHER.
- HUH?
- I SAID TAKE IT OFF!
- WHAT IF I DON'T
FEEL LIKE IT?
- UNDRESS!
- AVERT THEE EYES!
- HUH?
- MAYHAP YE LIKE EACH OTHER
MORE THAN I FIRST THOUGHT.
- EH?
- HUH?
[GRUNTING]
- HEY!
- I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT
YOU'D HAVE FIGURED OUT BY NOW
THAT MY BODY'S DIFFERENT.
[GASPS]
- IT'S ALREADY GONE!
- OH, SO GREAT A WOUND
TO HAVE HEALED SO QUICKLY
AND LEAVE NO SCAR.
- LOOK, JUST BECAUSE
IT WOULD HAVE KILLED A HUMAN
DON'T MAKE IT A BIG DEAL
FOR SOMEONE LIKE ME.
- HE'S NOT ALL HUMAN
BUT NOT DEMON EITHER.
CAN SOMEONE BE HALF?
- OW!
HUH?
[SUCKING]
- GREETINGS AND SALUTATIONS.
OH!
- HMM.
WELL, IF IT AIN'T
MYOGA THE FLEA.
- FLEA?
- SO, WHAT'D YOU COME
TO SEE ME ABOUT?
- LORD INUYASHA,
I'VE COME TO, UH...
I'VE COME TO TELL YOU THAT--
[SIGHS]
- WHAT'S THAT DO?
- UH, WHOOPS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, SOMEONE'S
TRYING TO FIND MY DAD'S TOMB?
- AS GUARDIAN OF
HIS FINAL RESTING PLACE,
I CAN BEAR IT NO LONGER.
- SO YOU TOOK OFF
AND CAME HERE INSTEAD.
- BUT IT'S THE REMAINS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT,
AND THEY ARE NO LONGER THERE.
- OH, SO WHERE ARE
THE REMAINS THEN?
- REGRETTABLY, SIRE,
NO ONE KNOWS.
- SOME GUARDIAN YOU ARE.
- INUYASHA, THEY SAY YOUR
FATHER WAS A PHANTOM BEAST,
THAT THE WESTERN LANDS
WERE HIS DOMAIN.
[SHOUTING]
- CAN'T SAY AS
I REMEMBER IT THAT WELL.
- YOUR FATHER WAS
A DEMON AMONG DEMONS,
GREAT AND POWERFUL.
HIS BLOOD WAS
ESPECIALLY DELICIOUS,
AND YOU, LORD INUYASHA, HAVE
INHERITED THAT FROM HIM.
- WOW!
AND WHAT ABOUT HIS MOM?
- SHE WAS A BEAUTY
BEYOND COMPARE,
A TRUE--UGH!
- HEY!
THAT WASN'T VERY NICE!
- JUST DROP IT, OK?
SHE DIED A LONG TIME AGO.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
DID SOMETHING I SAY
MAKE HIM UPSET?
- AYE, WELL...
- I'M SORRY.
ALL I DID WAS...ASK HIM
ABOUT...HIS MOTHER.
- YES. LORD INUYASHA HAS ALWAYS
PREFERRED NOT TO SPEAK OF HER.
- HIS FATHER WAS ALL DEMON,
BUT INUYASHA'S ONLY HALF.
IF ONE PART IS ONE THING,
THEN HIS OTHER HALF IS...
HUMAN?
THAT'S WHY!
- HMM!
HALF DEMON, HALF POWER.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
DISAPPOINTED?
I'LL BET YOU WERE HOPING TO USE
THIS TO BECOME ALL DEMON.
- HALF DEMON...
BUT HALF HUMAN, TOO.
THAT MUST BE WHY
HE'S ALWAYS SO...
HIS MOM WAS HUMAN, TOO.
- JUST DROP IT, OK?
SHE DIED A LONG TIME AGO.
- IS THAT WHY
HE WON'T TALK ABOUT IT?
- HIS MOM'S HUMAN,
SO HE HATES HER?
- SEE YOU LATER!
- KAGOME, WAIT!
- MOM, I CAN'T.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
- TAKE THIS.
I KNOW YOU'VE A LOT
TO CARRY, BUT I...
- MOM, I'VE GOT
TOO MUCH ALREADY.
- YOU CAN USE IT
FOR THAT FRIEND OF YOURS,
THE ONE WITH THE CUTE EARS.
DIDN'T YOU SAY HE'D BEEN
HURT IN THE SHOULDER?
- THANKS.
BUT THAT'S AWFUL.
HOW COULD SOMEONE HATE
THEIR OWN MOM?
BET SHE REALLY LOVES HIM.
HUH?
- GET DOWN!
[GRUNTS]
- INUYASHA!
- SOMETHING'S COMING.
CAN YOU FEEL IT?
- UH...OH!
A CARRIAGE?
THERE'S A LADY RIDING IN IT.
INUYASHA, WHAT'S WRONG?
- M-MOTHER!
- HUH?
- IT IS YOU!
INUYASHA!
AAH!
- MOTHER!
- IT CAN'T BE.
YOUR MOTHER'S DEAD.
YOU TOLD ME THAT YOURSELF.
- INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
[GASPS]
[ROARING]
- OH, NO!
HE'S GOING TO HURT YOUR MOM!
- NO, HE'S NOT!
UGH! UGH!
[GRUNTS]
YOU MISSED!
- JAKEN.
- YES, MILORD?
- ONCE WE'RE THROUGH,
I WANT HIM DEAD.
- YES, MILORD.
- IT IS YOU.
SESSHOMARU!
- INDEED.
I'VE QUITE MISSED YOU
AS WELL...LITTLE BROTHER.
- IT IS YOU.
SESSHOMARU!
- INDEED.
I'VE QUITE MISSED YOU
AS WELL...LITTLE BROTHER.
- HE CALLED YOU HIS BROTHER.
DOES THAT MEAN HE'S--
- HMM. A MORTAL.
HOW INTERESTING.
- YEAH. WHAT OF IT?
- OTHERS WOULD BE SHAMED,
BUT WITH YOU, LITTLE BROTHER,
THE GIRL QUITE SUITS YOU.
- OH! OH!
- THESE HUMAN CREATURES...
I SHOULD THINK
YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THEM.
OR IS IT A TASTE
FROM FATHER?
[GROWLING]
- SO HIS MOTHER IS HUMAN THEN.
- THAT'S NOT ALL, IS IT?
YOU COULDN'T HAVE COME ALL
THIS WAY JUST TO TELL ME THAT.
- BE NOT A FOOL.
I HAVE NO SUCH TIME TO WASTE.
THE TOMB OF OUR FATHER--
WHERE MUST I SEEK IT?
- OUR FATHER'S TOMB?
WHY ASK ME?
- SEEING YET NEVER SEEN,
PROTECTED YET NEVER KNOWN
TO ITS PROTECTOR.
NO OTHER CLUES ARE KNOWN.
- I GOT NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
BESIDES, EVEN IF I DID,
THERE'S NO WAY I'D TELL YOU!
- I SEE.
THEN YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE
BUT TO LET YOUR MOTHER'S
SUFFERING CONVINCE YOU.
[MOANING]
[GASPS]
- INUYASHA!
- HUH. NICE TRY, JERK!
SHE'S BEEN DEAD FOR YEARS,
AND WE BOTH KNOW IT!
LIKE I'D REALLY FALL FOR
SOME STUPID TRICK LIKE THAT!
- A TRICK, IS IT?
- YOU'RE WHO'S STUPID.
RECALLING SPIRITS
FROM THE NETHERWORLD
IS A SIMPLE TASK,
IF YOU ARE LORD SESSHOMARU.
HE WAS EVEN SO KIND
AS TO GIVE HER FLESH,
AND YET HER OWN SON
WOULD DENY IT.
HOW SAD TO BE MOTHER
TO ONE SUCH AS YOU!
[MOANING]
- INUYASHA!
- THEN MAYBE...IT IS TRUE!
- I HAVE COME BACK,
INUYASHA!
BACK FROM THE WORLD
OF THE DEAD!
[GROANING]
- STOP HURTING HER!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
[GRUNTS]
[SQUEAKING]
- OH, NO!
ARE YOU OK?
- KAGOME! YOU AND HER,
GET OUT OF HERE!
- I THINK NOT.
AND YOU...
YOU'RE WORTHLESS!
[GASPS]
- MOTHER!
- INUYASHA!
- AAH!
[SHOUTING]
AAH! AAH!
- WHAT A BOTHER.
- AYE, MILORD,
AND YET IT GOES SO WELL.
PLEASE, MILORD,
LEAVE IT ALL TO ME.
- THIS SCHEME OF YOURS
IS BENEATH ME.
SHOULD IT FAIL, JAKEN,
YOU WILL DIE.
- AAH!
AS YOU WILL, MILORD.
[GROANING]
- THIS PLACE...
WHERE IS IT?
- AT THE BORDER
OF THE SPIRIT WORLD.
- HUH?
- I MUST BE CROSSING
OVER IT VERY SOON.
- CROSSING OVER?
- OH, YEAH. RIGHT.
IT HAPPENED SO LONG AGO,
I KEEP FORGETTING YOU'RE DEAD.
- INUYASHA, YOU...
YOU'VE BECOME A MAN,
HAVEN'T YOU?
- WELL, YEAH.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU DIED, I GUESS
I WAS STILL JUST A KID, RIGHT?
- SUCH TERRIBLE,
VIOLENT DAYS,
AND YOU ALL ALONE
WITH NO ONE TO CARE FOR YOU.
HOW CAN YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?
- IT WEREN'T
THAT BIG A DEAL.
I MEAN...
- INUYASHA.
- HUH?
[MOANING]
- INUYASHA'S MOTHER.
SHE'S OK.
UH...I...
I CAN'T MOVE.
I'M PARALYZED.
[GASPING]
HER FACE! NO REFLECTION!
INUYASHA! INU--
MY VOICE! I CAN'T SPEAK!
- MOTHER.
- PARTINGS ARE NEVER EASY.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- I...
- INUYASHA!
SNAP OUT OF IT!
SHE DOESN'T HAVE A FACE!
WHOEVER SHE IS,
SHE'S NOT YOUR MOM!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- TO SAVE HIS MOM,
INUYASHA RISKED HIS LIFE.
FROM THE KINDS OF CLOTHES
SHE'S WEARING,
I'D HAVE TO SAY HE'S FROM
A SUPER, MEGA RICH FAMILY,
NOT THAT YOU CAN TELL
FROM THE WAY HE TALKS.
HOW AWFUL THAT
SESSHOMARU WOULD USE
INUYASHA'S FEELINGS
FOR HIS MOM TO SET A TRAP.
I'M TELLING YOU
FOR THE LAST TIME,
THAT WOMAN IS NOT YOUR MOM!
NEXT TIME, "TETSUSAIGA,
THE PHANTOM SWORD."
SEE YOU SOON!