- 3, 2, 1.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT.
YOUR NOODLES ARE READY.
[SLURPING]
- NOT BAD. NOT BAD.
I CAN SEE HOW THIS
WOULD CATCH ON.
- NEXT BEST THING
TO SLICED BREAD.
- COME ON, KAGOME.
AREN'T YOU GONNA DIG IN?
[GROWLS]
- SPEAKING OF DIGGING,
HAVE YOU NOTICED
WE'RE SURROUNDED BY
CORPSES HERE?
NO, I GUESS
YOU WERE TOO BUSY
RUMMAGING THROUGH
MY BACKPACK TO REALIZE
THAT WE HAPPEN TO BE SITTING
IN AN OLD BATTLEFIELD.
"I'M HUNGRY," HE SAYS.
THEN HE HAS THE NERVE
TO EXPECT ME TO EAT HERE!
JEEZ!
EVEN YOUR BLOOD-SUCKING
FLEA BUDDY HAS BETTER MANNERS.
- FINALLY, I FOUND SOMEONE
WHO HAS GOOD TASTE
AND TASTES GOOD.
I MUST SAY
HOW IMPRESSED I AM
BY THE CONVENIENCES
OF YOUR ERA--
THAT BIKE-CYCLE
AND YOUR INSTANT FOODSTUFFS.
TELL ME, HAS OUR LAND
STARTED TRADING
WITH OTHER LANDS?
- YEAH!
GOOD OBSERVATION, MYOGA.
FIGURES YOU'D NOTICE.
ACTUALLY, INSTANT
NOODLES WERE INVENTED
RIGHT HERE IN JAPAN
DURING THE SPACE AGE.
EVERYONE EATS THEM,
BUT ORIGINALLY THEY WERE MEANT
FOR ASTRONAUTS IN OUTER SPACE.
- ASTRO-NUTS?
- ASTRONAUTS.
WE'VE EXPLORED OUTER SPACE.
HEY, RIGHT!
I GUESS YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WE'VE BEEN TO THE MOON.
- MAN HAS TRAVELED
TO THE MOON?
- ON A BI-CYCLE?
- NO. IN A ROCKET,
OF COURSE.
- AND A ROCKET WOULD BE...
- THEY'RE LONG
AND THEY'RE USUALLY WHITE,
AND FLAMES
SHOOT OUT THE BOTTOM.
COUNTDOWN TO LAUNCH!
ZOOM!
LIFTOFF!
TRUST YOU TO BE
MORE IMPRESSED BY NOODLES
THAN BY SPACE TRAVEL.
OH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY IS IT SO DARK?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT SOMETHING TELLS ME
IT'S TROUBLE.
- LORD INUYASHA,
NO LITTERING.
- THIS IS NO TIME
TO TALK TRASH.
- YOU DOWN THERE.
YOU POSSESS A PIECE
OF THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL.
- WHO'S THAT?
- A DEMON?
- I BELIEVE IT'S A FOX.
- NOT LIKELY, MYOGA.
- HUH?
- HAND OVER THE JEWEL.
THE JEWEL OR YOUR LIFE.
WHOA!
[GROANS]
- IT'S A KID.
- WHO DARES
TO BURST MY BUBBLE?
OH!
- HMM.
FEISTY LITTLE THING,
AREN'T YOU?
NICE TAIL.
LOOKS LIKE A BADGER
OR A SQUIRREL.
- I'M A FOX, HEATHEN!
- A FOX? IT TALKS.
COOL.
LET ME TOUCH HIM
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
- YOU MIND?
I'M TRYING
TO TEACH HIM A LESSON.
- WHERE'D THAT COME FROM?
[PANTING]
HEY, GET OUT OF MY STUFF!
- FOUND IT!
A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
OUR TIME TOGETHER
HAS BEEN SHORT BUT SWEET.
FAREWELL.
- HUH?
- HE DISAPPEARED.
[GROWLS]
- ALWAYS PICK ON
THE LITTLE GUY.
- THIS MIGHT STING A BIT.
JUST THINK HAPPY THOUGHTS.
SO WHY WERE YOU SO DETERMINED
TO GET THE JEWEL FROM US?
- FOR MY FATHER.
I NEED TO GET
THE SHARDS OF THE JEWEL
TO AVENGE HIM.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "AVENGE"?
YOU DON'T MEAN
YOUR FATHER WAS KILLED, DO YOU?
- I GET IT.
HE'S NOT STRONG ENOUGH,
SO HE NEEDS THE POWER
OF THE JEWEL
TO TAKE OUT HIS ENEMIES.
- HMM?
- I'M STRONG ENOUGH
TO TAKE ON AN ENEMY.
I WANTED THE JEWEL
AS A PRECAUTION.
- I WAS PROTECTING IT FOR YOU.
- HEY!
I DO THE TALKING HERE!
- HMM?
- IT ALL STARTED
NOT TOO LONG AGO.
HUNDREDS OF WARRIORS
WERE ENGAGED IN A BATTLE
NEAR THE FOREST
WHERE WE LIVED,
WHEN A DARK CLOUD
PASSED OVERHEAD--
A CLOUD SO DARK AND EVIL
NONE COULD IMAGINE
WHAT HORRORS IT WOULD BRING.
THE WARRIORS
WERE AT FIRST PUZZLED
BY THE STRANGE TURN
IN THE WEATHER.
- LOOK! SOMETHING APPROACHES!
- TIME TO HUNT, MANTEN.
- AYE, BROTHER.
START THE HUNT.
[SHOUTING]
- FLEE, LITTLE RODENTS.
- THEY ANNIHILATED THE ENEMY
WITH A SINGLE STRIKE
OF LIGHTNING.
[GASPING]
WHAT IS THEIR PURPOSE?
DO THE BEASTS
CLAIM TO BE OUR ALLIES?
- HMM.
YOU ENTERTAIN THOUGHTS
OF BEING OUR ALLIES?
[ROARS]
[MEN SHOUTING]
- AHH. THAT WAS CERTAINLY
ENTERTAINING.
- YES, INDEED.
PITIFUL WARRIORS.
- BUT THE DAY IS STILL YOUNG
AND I'M FEELING RESTLESS.
THE SHIKON JEWEL SHARD
EMBEDDED IN MY FOREHEAD
LEAVES ME
WITH POWER TO SPARE.
- SO TRUE.
- IMAGINE WHAT POWERS
WE WOULD HAVE
WITH EVEN MORE JEWELS.
- WE MUST SEARCH
AMONG THE BEASTS
AND RELINQUISH THEM
OF THEIR PRECIOUS TREASURES,
AS WE DID
WITH OUR DEARLY DEPARTED
FRIEND THE FOX.
[LAUGHING EVILLY]
- WAIT, THEY MURDERED
YOUR FATHER
TO GET HIS SHARD
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL?
BUT WHY DID HE HAVE IT?
- I COULDN'T SAY.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
THE THUNDER BROTHERS
STEAL THE JEWELS
FROM DEMONS.
- THUNDER BROTHERS?
- IT'S A NICKNAME--
BECAUSE OF THEIR THUNDER
AND LIGHTNING ATTACKS.
- HEARD OF 'EM, MYOGA?
- HE MUST BE TALKING
ABOUT HITEN AND MANTEN.
AND IF THE RUMORS ARE TRUE,
THOSE TWO ARE EVIL
INCARNATE.
- BIG DEAL.
ALL I GOTTA DO
IS DEFEAT THE BROTHERS
AND I'LL WALK AWAY
WITH ALL THEIR JEWEL SHARDS.
- AND ONE DAY MAN
WILL WALK ON THE MOON.
YOU'RE NOT MATCH
FOR THE EVIL THUNDER BROTHERS.
YOU'RE ONLY HALF-DEMON.
I CAN SMELL
THE HUMAN IN YOU.
THIS IS BETWEEN DEMONS.
IT'S GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH HALF-BREEDS
SUCH AS YOURSELF.
STAY OUT OF IT.
- THAT'S NO WAY
TO SPEAK TO INUYASHA.
- OH!
YOU BIG--
- GO EASY ON HIM.
- FORGIVE ME.
NO HARD FEELINGS.
VERY SORRY.
- SOMEONE'S GOTTA
TEACH HIM A LESSON.
AS A TOKEN OF MY APOLOGY--
[CHUCKLES]
- THIS SUPPOSED
TO BE HUMOROUS?
- HEH HEH HEH.
YOU'RE STUCK UNTIL YOU CAN GET
THE SPELL SCROLL PEELED OFF.
- DON'T BE SO CHILDISH, SHIPPO.
TAKE THE SPELL OFF HIM.
COME ON, INUYASHA.
THE STATUE
CAN'T BE THAT HEAVY.
- I'D LIKE TO SEE
YOU FREE YOURSELF.
AAH!
- I DON'T LIKE
PLAYING TRICKS ON WOMEN
IF I CAN AVOID IT.
DON'T HOLD THIS AGAINST ME,
KAGOME.
- A LITTLE RESPECT, PLEASE.
NOT AGAIN.
- THANKS!
I'LL USE THIS TO LURE OUT
THE THUNDER BROTHERS.
- HEY! THAT LITTLE DOG.
HE'S GOT MY JEWEL SHARD AGAIN.
GET BACK HERE,
YOU MANGY MUTT!
- WAIT! KAGOME!
YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE ME
STUCK LIKE THIS.
WAIT!
KAGOME!
- HMM.
WHAT A PLEASING VISAGE.
BUT WITH A FEW MORE HAIRS
I COULD ATTRACT THE LADIES
AS BROTHER HITEN DOES.
HMM?
- THEY'LL NEVER FIND ME NOW.
OH!
- MMM.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
IF IT ISN'T THE SON
OF THAT FLEA-BITTEN FOX.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
AAH!
- LIKE MY FUR COAT, DO YOU?
JUST LIKE YOUR FATHER'S.
HA HA HA!
- MONSTER!
YOU'LL PAY
FOR WHAT YOU DID.
LET ME AT YOU!
- HUH? OOH!
A SHARD OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
NOW HAND IT OVER
LIKE A GOOD LITTLE LAD,
OR ELSE...
- DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
- HEH HEH HEH!
- WOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I HIT HIM.
- WHY YOU...
AND AS FOR YOU...
- STAY RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
- HUH?
- I'VE GOT AN ARROW HERE
AND I'M NOT AFRAID
TO USE IT.
- PLEASE, GET THIS THING OFF ME!
[GASPS]
- A MONSTER!
- HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I NEED YOU TO PEEL OFF
THIS SPELL SCROLL.
- KAGOME.
- MY BEAUTIFUL NOSE.
- DON'T MOVE AN INCH,
OR WHATEVER.
SHIPPO, GET OVER HERE,
AND BRING THE JEWEL SHARD
WITH YOU.
- STOP!
I MUST HAVE
THAT SHIKON JEWEL.
- HE HAS TWO JEWEL FRAGMENTS
IN HIS FOREHEAD.
IF I HIT HIM THERE,
I CAN BRING HIM DOWN.
CLOSE, BUT I JUST GRAZED HIM.
[WHIMPERING]
WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
- AAH!
- COME ON! WE GOTTA FLEE!
THAT'S THE SAME KIND OF ATTACK
THAT KILLED MY DAD.
- WHOA!
- THAT SHOULD STOP THEM
FOR AWHILE.
- KAGOME,
YOU'VE GOTTA GET UP.
- SO THE LITTLE FOX
MANAGED TO ESCAPE.
HUH?
SHE LOOKS GOOD ENOUGH TO EAT.
SHE'S LOVELY.
[THUNDER]
- HE HAS KAGOME.
I'VE GOTTA GO RESCUE HER.
BUT HOW?
I DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THE THUNDER BROTHERS.
KAGOME WILL SOON
BE IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
UNLESS...
- IT'S NO USE, MILORD.
I CAN'T REMOVE
THE SPELL SCROLL.
- WHY THAT LITTLE FOX!
HE'LL REGRET
DOING THIS TO ME!
- INUYASHA,
I'LL HELP YOU
ON ONE CONDITION--
WHICH IS YOU PROMISE
NOT TO HIT ME ANYMORE.
- WHERE'S KAGOME?
WHY DIDN'T
SHE COME BACK WITH YOU?
- WILL YOU PROMISE ME
OR WON'T YOU?
- OK, I WON'T STRIKE YOU.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TELL YOU WHERE SHE IS.
I THOUGHT WE HAD A PROMISE.
- HMM.
OH, RIGHT.
THAT REMINDS ME.
YOU HAVE SOMETHING
THAT BELONGS TO ME.
UH-HUH.
THANK GOODNESS.
IT'S SAFE.
- WOULD YOU FORGET THAT
FOR AWHILE?
KAGOME'S BEEN ABDUCTED
BY THE THUNDER BROTHERS.
SO SHOULDN'T
YOU GO AFTER HER?
- HUH?
THE SAME TWO BROTHERS
WHO KILLED YOUR FATHER
ABDUCTED KAGOME?
YOU LET 'EM GET AWAY?
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY
REEKING OF THE SCENT
OF VICTORY.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
CONCEAL YOURSELF IN THE BUSHES
WHILE THEY MADE OFF WITH HER?
- WHY DO YOU PIN
ALL THE BLAME ON ME?
SHE'S YOUR WOMAN.
YOU SHOULD DO
AT LEAST SOME OF THE RESCUING.
- HUH?
- SHE AIN'T MY WOMAN!
HMPH!
- HEY!
- BUT I SUPPOSE
IT WOULDN'T HURT
TO SAVE HER.
- HUH?
- IF YOU'RE PREPARED
TO GIVE ME AN APOLOGY, THAT IS--
AND ALSO PREPARE ME
A NICE, HOT BATH TONIGHT.
[GROWLS]
- SHIPPO, GIVE THE MASTER
WHAT HE WANTS.
TIME IS WASTING
AND THE GIRL IS IN DANGER.
- WHY AM I ALWAYS THE ONE
HANDING OUT APOLOGIES?
BUT I CAN'T RESCUE KAGOME
ON MY OWN.
OK!
I APOLOGIZE.
- DON'T MENTION IT.
COME ON,
WE GOT A LOT OF WORK
TO DO, SHIPPO.
LET'S MOVE OUT.
- THAT WAS FAIRLY PAINLESS.
- MMM.
HEH HEH HEH.
AH, MOTHER WOULD BE PROUD
IF SHE KNEW THE FAMILY RECIPE
WAS BEING PUT TO USE.
THE ONLY INGREDIENT LEFT TO ADD
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT ONE--
THE ONE I LIKE TO CALL
DELICIOUSLY AWFUL.
HA HA HA!
- HUH?
HUH?
- AWOKEN, HAVE YOU,
MY FAIR MAIDEN?
- WHERE HAVE YOU TAKEN ME?
- THAT'S THE LEAST
OF YOUR WORRIES.
- WHY ARE YOU LOOKING AT ME
THAT WAY?
- I WILL TELL YOU.
THE FLESH AND BLOOD
OF YOUNG MAIDENS
DOES MARVELS
FOR HAIR GROWTH.
SOME CALL IT
THE WONDER POTION
OF THE CENTURY.
[SQUEALS]
- I'D RATHER BE EATEN ALIVE
THAN BOILED DOWN
FOR SOME HAIR CONCOCTION!
- SHH!
KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN.
IF BROTHER HITEN HEARS YOU,
HE MIGHT JUST
FULFILL YOUR WISH.
[GASPS]
- THOUGHT I HEARD VOICES.
BACK SO SOON, MANTEN?
- UH, THAT THING
IS YOUR BROTHER?
- HITEN, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- WHO'S SHE?
WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
- SHE'S MINE!
I FOUND HER FIRST!
- NO NEED TO WORRY.
I HAVE NO USE FOR HER.
NOT WHEN I HAVE
THIS LITTLE VIXEN.
[PURRS]
- AT LEAST THAT BROTHER
LOOKS HUMAN.
MAYBE I CAN TALK MY WAY
OUT OF THIS.
- OH, WHILE
I'M THINKING ABOUT IT,
HOW'D YOU FARE
IN YOUR SEARCH FOR MORE
JEWEL FRAGMENTS?
- HUH?
[SWALLOWS]
HOW COULD I HAVE FORGOTTEN?
[GROWLS]
MY APOLOGIES, DEAR BROTHER.
I FOUND ONE,
BUT I LOST IT.
- FOUND ONE BUT LOST IT?
DON'T TELL ME
YOU WERE MORE INTERESTED
IN THIS WOMAN,
SO MUCH THAT
YOU FORGOT ALL ABOUT
THE PRECIOUS JEWEL SHARD.
- PLEASE, HITEN.
FORGIVE ME.
- YOU BRING NOTHING
BUT SHAME TO THIS FAMILY.
IF YOU WERE NOT
MY YOUNGER BROTHER,
I WOULD'VE DONE YOU IN
LONG AGO.
- THEN AGAIN,
LOOKS CAN BE DECEIVING.
OH, MAN,
I'M IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
- SO, THIS LITTLE SHIPPO TYKE
HAS OUR JEWEL SHARD?
- ARE YOU GOING AFTER HIM?
- OF COURSE I AM.
AND YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
- THIS IS MY CHANCE
TO TRY AND ESCAPE.
- WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
- AAH!
HEY, WATCH WHERE
YOU'RE AIMING THAT!
- 1,000 PARDONS.
I MEANT TO MAKE IT QUICK
SO YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO SUFFER.
AND THERE'S NO SENSE DELAYING,
SINCE I WOULDN'T WANT
THE MAIN INGREDIENT
FOR MY HAIR POTION ESCAPING.
- WAIT!
YOU DON'T WANT TO KILL ME!
- AND WHY NOT?
- UH, BECAUSE
YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO FIND SHIPPO
AND HIS SHARD OF THE JEWEL.
- HUH?
- THERE'S ONE BORN
EVERY MINUTE.
I'VE CONVINCED THE DUMB ONE.
NOW FOR HIS BROTHER.
YEAH, I CAN DO THIS.
- ARE YOU TWO FAMILIAR
WITH INUYASHA,
THE STRONG, BRAVE,
HANDSOME WARRIOR?
- HIM, STRONG?
THAT INUYASHA'S
MERELY A HALF-DEMON.
- BUT HE IS STRONG.
HE'S DEFEATED
ALL KINDS OF MONSTERS
SINGLE-HANDED.
AND MORE TO THE POINT,
HE HAS MOST OF THE FRAGMENTS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
- HUH?
- GO, GIRL.
THAT SURE GOT
THEIR ATTENTION.
- YOU...
ARE YOU LYING?
[GIGGLES]
- I WOULDN'T LIE ABOUT HIM.
THE GUY'S
MADLY IN LOVE WITH ME.
- HMM.
- IF YOU TELL HIM
YOU'RE HOLDING ME CAPTIVE,
I KNOW MY ONE AND ONLY LOVE
WILL GLADLY HAND OVER
THE JEWELS.
- SOMETHING TELLS ME
SHE'S LYING.
- I THINK
SHE'S TELLING THE TRUTH.
- WHA--
- WENCH!
TAKE US TO THE INUYASHA
LOVER OF YOURS AT ONCE.
BUT BE WARNED,
IF YOU'RE LYING,
YOU'LL SUFFER
THE SAME FATE AS SHE...
AND I DOUBT YOU'D ENJOY
BEING FRIED TO A CRISP.
- THIS GUY WOULD DO IT, TOO,
AND PROBABLY ENJOY IT.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, SHIPPO?
NO AFRAID OF HEIGHTS,
ARE YOU?
I COULD ALWAYS TAKE YOU BACK
IF YOU'RE FRIGHTENED.
- I'M NOT AFRAID.
WHOA!
I'M GONNA SAVE KAGOME
AND AVENGE FATHER.
WITH A LITTLE HELP
FROM YOU, THAT IS.
YOU BETTER BE AS STRONG
AS YOU SAY YOU ARE.
THOSE THUNDER BROTHERS
HAVE JEWELS IN THEIR FOREHEADS
THAT MAKE THEM POWERFUL.
WHOA!
- HEH HEH.
THAT'LL ONLY MAKE DEFEATING THEM
MORE ENJOYABLE.
- MASTER, WE MUST HURRY BEFORE
THEY DO SOMETHING TO KAGOME.
- I'M SURE
SHE CAN HANDLE HERSELF.
SHE'S PROBABLY GOT THEM
CLEANING THEIR CAVE.
- WE CAN ONLY HOPE.
BUT IF THE RUMORS
ARE TO BE BELIEVED,
THE THUNDER BROTHERS
DO NOT KEEP PRETTY
YOUNG LADIES FOR LONG
BEFORE DEVOURING THEM.
- DEVOURING THEM?
INUYASHA,
DO YOU SUPPOSE KAGOME IS--
- GET REAL.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR HIM?
HE SAID "PRETTY"
YOUNG LADIES.
- YEAH? SHE IS PRETTY--
AND BRAVE, AND SMART.
- HMM.
ISN'T ANYONE
GONNA ASK MY OPINION?
- OH, THIS IS ALL MY FAULT!
SHE'S PROBABLY BEING
EATEN ALIVE AS WE SPEAK.
- METHINKS PERHAPS
IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
- IF IT'S NOT TOO MUCH TROUBLE,
COULD WE CONTINUE THE SEARCH?
WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GET TO KAGOME
BEFORE THE THUNDER BROTHERS
GET HUNGRY.
- WHAT'S THE RUSH?
SHE AIN'T PRETTY,
SO THEY'RE DEFINITELY
NOT GONNA GO FOR HER.
- WE CAN ALWAYS
TAKE A VOTE.
AND SEEING AS I HAVE
4 HANDS INSTEAD OF 2,
I SHOULD BE ALLOWED
TO VOTE TWICE.
- AAH!
SHE'LL COME BACK
AND HAUNT ME FOR THIS.
I'VE HEARD THE LEGENDS
AND I KNOW HOW IT WORKS.
- I DID SAY
"PRETTY YOUNG LADIES,"
IT'S TRUE,
AND BEAUTY IS IN THE EYE
OF THE BEHOLDER,
AND SHIPPO MIGHT FIND HER
GOOD-LOOKING.
I MYSELF AM FOND OF
MORE FLESHY WOMEN--
- QUIT NAGGING!
I'M GOING, ALL RIGHT!
STOP YAPPING AT ME
AND JUST POINT THE WAY
TO THE EVIL BROTHERS!
[SCREAMING]
- VERY IMPRESSIVE MANEUVER,
DODGING MY LIGHTNING BOLT,
ESPECIALLY IN LIGHT
OF YOUR DULL AND UNINSPIRED
CONVERSATION JUST NOW.
YOU MUST BE
THE REPUTED INUYASHA HIMSELF.
- MASTER INUYASHA,
THAT IS HITEN, THE ELDER
OF THE THUNDER BROTHERS.
- WHERE'S KAGOME?
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE WITH HER?
- DON'T DESPAIR.
WE HAVE DONE NOTHING TO HER
AS OF YET.
- MANTEN.
- COMING, BROTHER.
BEHOLD.
- INUYASHA!
- KAGOME!
WELL, AT LEAST
THEY HAVEN'T HURT HER...
YET.
- JUDGING BY YOUR EXPRESSION,
IT SEEMS THE GIRL
SPOKE THE TRUTH.
NOW HAND OVER THE FRAGMENTS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL TO ME
OR YOU'LL NEVER SEE
YOUR LOVE ALIVE AGAIN!
- SEE MY LOVER?
- SOME PEOPLE
JUST CAN'T TAKE A JOKE.
- UH, THERE MUST BE
SOME MISUNDERSTANDING.
LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU AND I
ARE SUPPOSED TO BE LOVERS?
- THIS IS NO TIME
TO GET ALL SHY!
- YOU LITTLE VIXEN.
I KNEW YOU WERE FIBBING.
[WHIMPERS]
- YOU ACTUALLY THINK
I'D HAND OVER THE JEWEL SHARDS
AS A RANSOM
TO GET YOU BACK?
- OF COURSE YOU WOULD,
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT
A LOVER WOULD DO!
- BUT WE AIN'T LOVERS!
AND WITHOUT LOVE,
THE WHOLE ARGUMENT
KIND OF FALLS APART.
- SO NOW SOME LITTLE GEMS
ARE MORE IMPORTANT THAN ME?
HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT
AFTER ALL
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH TOGETHER.
IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU'D BETTER ADMIT TO YOURSELF
HOW MUCH YOU REALLY LOVE ME!
- I BELIEVE
I'VE HEARD MY FILL.
IT'S CLEAR THAT
YOU DO HAVE SOME JEWELS
FOR US, INUYASHA.
JEWELS THAT WILL BE MINE!
- NOT IN MY LIFETIME, PAL.
- NO ONE CAN WITHSTAND
MY ATTACKS FOR VERY LONG.
YOU DO HAVE POWER,
BUT NO STYLE.
THIS SHOULD BE
AN INTERESTING BATTLE.
- AND HOPEFULLY YOUR LAST.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- SHIPPO, THE LITTLE FOX,
IS DESPERATE TO AVENGE
HIS FATHER'S DEATH.
IF INUYASHA'S HALF THE WARRIOR
HE KEEPS TELLING US HE IS,
HE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO HELP SHIPPO
DEFEAT THE THUNDER BROTHERS.
BUT WHEN THE 5 JEWEL FRAGMENTS
FALL INTO THE ENEMY HANDS,
SOMETHING TERRIBLE HAPPENS,
AND AN EVEN MORE DEMONIC MONSTER
CONFRONTS INUYASHA.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!