[SNARLING]
- YAAHHH!
[HOWLING]
- AAH!
- HOW DARE YOU?
- UH...
- WHY DID YOU SLAUGHTER
MY PACK OF WOLVES?
- 3 SHARDS!
HE HAS ONE ON HIS RIGHT ARM
AND ONE ON EACH LEG!
INUYASHA, WATCH OUT.
HE HAS 3 SHARDS.
- SO YOU'RE THE ONE CONTROLLING
THIS BLOODTHIRSTY PACK.
- AND YOU'RE THEIR EXECUTIONER.
DAMN YOU ALL
FOR MURDERING MY UNDERLINGS.
YOU'LL PAY WITH YOUR LIVES.
- GO ON, TRY IT.
HOW MANY INNOCENT PEOPLE HAVE
YOU AND YOUR MONGRELS KILLED?
YOU REEK OF HUMAN BLOOD.
- THEY NEEDED TO EAT.
GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT,
MUTT-FACE?
- DID YOU JUST CALL ME
A MUTT?
- NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT WOULD BE AN INSULT
TO CANINES.
YOU SMELL MUCH WORSE!
- HUH.
DON'T LIKE MY SMELL?
THEN MAYBE I'LL SOLVE
YOUR PROBLEM
BY SLICING OFF YOUR NOSE
AND STABBING SOME AIR
INTO YOUR BELLY!
YAH! HYAH!
- HYAH!
- HUH?
- HEH!
UHH!
- AAH!
- UNREAL.
- HE'S FAST.
- INUYASHA, WATCH OUT!
HE'S USING THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
THEY'RE ON HIS LEGS
AND RIGHT ARM!
- SHE CAN TELL!
- WHY DIDN'T YOU
SAY SO EARLIER?
HUH. I THOUGHT
YOU WERE ACTING PRETTY TOUGH,
BUT IT'S ONLY 'CAUSE
YOU'VE GOT JEWEL SHARDS.
YOU HAVEN'T GOT ANY POWER
ON YOUR OWN, DO YOU?
- HEH! BUT YOU'VE GOT TO
KNOW HOW TO USE THE POWER,
YOU WHINING WHELP.
- IF ONLY YOU COULD FIGHT
AS FAST AS YOU CAN TALK,
THEN WE'D GET SOMEWHERE.
- SHUT UP, ALBINO RUNT!
- YOU OUGHT TO BE PUT DOWN
FOR RABIES!
- THEY'RE WELL-MATCHED
WHEN IT COMES TO FOUL BEHAVIOR.
- HE'S A WOLF DEMON.
- YOU'VE ENCOUNTERED THEM
BEFORE?
- I'M KOGA, THE NEW LEADER OF
THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE,
AND YOUR DESTROYER!
- I'VE HEARD ABOUT THEM
FROM OTHER DEMON SLAYERS.
THEY'RE DEMONS
WHO CONTROL WOLVES.
ALTHOUGH THEY APPEAR HUMAN,
THEY'RE NO DIFFERENT THAN
THE WOLVES THEY COMMAND.
[GROWLING]
- THEY'RE CLOSING IN
FROM EITHER SIDE!
- KIRARA!
[SNARLING]
[YELPING]
- THEY RAN OFF WITH THEIR TAIL
BETWEEN THEIR LEGS.
THE REST IS UP TO INUYASHA.
- AAH!
- TCH. WHAT A JOKE.
YOU COULD BARELY KEEP UP
ON THE DEFENSIVE,
LET ALONE ATTACK.
- HMM.
THIS WOULD BE THE PERFECT TIME
TO TEST MY TETSUSAIGA.
I'LL BLAST IT
ON THIS MANGY WOLF.
- [GRUNTING]
- AAH!
WHEN THE FLOW OF DARK ENERGY
COLLIDES WITH THE WIND,
IT CREATES A FISSURE.
I CAN PICK UP ITS SCENT.
THAT'S THE WIND SCAR.
LET THE TRUE POWER
OF TETSUSAIGA BE KNOWN!
- HUH?
- TETSUSAIGA!
- SOMETHING'S WRONG!
- HUH?
- [GASPING]
LET'S RETREAT.
THIS IS TOO DANGEROUS!
- DID HE...JUST RUN AWAY?
- HE DID.
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN JILTED.
- INUYASHA...
WERE YOU ABOUT TO USE
THE WIND SCAR IN BATTLE
WITH HIM?
- YEAH...
BUT THE COWARD
UP AND RAN AWAY.
I GUESS HE WAS ALL TALK
AND NO ACTION.
- MAKES ME WONDER.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WELL, I WONDER IF KOGA SENSED
THE POWER OF TETSUSAIGA
BEFORE IT HIT HIM.
MAYBE HIS INSTINCTS TOLD HIM
HE WAS IN DANGER.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN IT'S NOT JUST
BRUTE STRENGTH WE'RE UP AGAINST.
- [GRUNTS]
WELL, I THINK
THAT WAS THE LAST OF THEM.
- MAN, ALL WE SEEM
TO BE DOING LATELY
IS BURYING PEOPLE.
I'M BECOMING A PROFESSIONAL
GRAVEDIGGER,
EXCEPT THAT NO ONE'S
PAYING ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I GOT SUCKERED
INTO ANOTHER GOOD SAMARITAN ACT.
- IT SEEMS LIKE EVERY TIME
WE TRAVEL IN THE DIRECTION
IN WHICH KAGOME SENSES
A SACRED JEWEL SHARD,
WE COME ACROSS
ANOTHER VILLAGE
THAT'S BEEN COMPLETELY
ANNIHILATED.
[SIGHS]
THE BATTLE TO CLAIM
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
HAS WROUGHT NOTHING
BUT TRAGEDY,
AND COUNTLESS
INNOCENT VILLAGERS
HAVE LOST THEIR LIVES
BECAUSE OF IT.
- SO WHAT?
SO WHILE I BELIEVE
IT IS A WORTHWHILE VENTURE
TO TAKE POSSESSION
OF THE JEWEL SHARDS
BEFORE NARAKU
OR ANY OTHER DEMON CAN,
I CANNOT APPROVE OF
YOUR SEEKING THE SHARDS
IN ORDER TO USE THEIR POWER
TO BECOME A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
THAT IS ALL I'M SAYING.
- HUH!
DON'T START THAT UP AGAIN.
YOU'RE NOT WINNING POINTS
FOR PERSISTENCE.
I'M GONNA BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON
NO MATTER WHAT ANYBODY SAYS,
SO DON'T TRY TO STOP ME!
- THE POWER OF THE SACRED JEWEL
CAN BE USED FOR GOOD OR EVIL,
BUT THINK THINGS THROUGH
CAREFULLY, INUYASHA.
IN ALL OF OUR TRAVELS
TOGETHER,
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF ANYONE
WHO FOUND HAPPINESS
THROUGH THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL?
NO GOOD WILL COME OF IT.
IT IS A POWER FUELED BY
DARKNESS AND BLOOD.
- HAVE YOU HEARD OF
THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE
BEFORE, TOO?
- OH, YEAH.
THEY LIVE IN PACKS
UP IN THE MOUNTAINS,
AND THEY THINK
THEY'RE SUPREME WOLF DEMONS.
THEY BULLY OTHER DEMONS
OFF THEIR LAND
AND CLAIM IT
AS THEIR OWN TERRITORY.
SMALLER DEMONS LIKE ME
WERE DRIVEN OUT
AND HAD TO FIND SHELTER
ELSEWHERE
BECAUSE
THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE
TOOK POSSESSION
OF THE MOUNTAINS,
AND THEY GUARD THEM
RUTHLESSLY.
- INTERESTING.
SO, HAVE YOU HEARD OF
THIS KOGA BEFORE?
- UH, THERE ARE SO MANY BRANCHES
OF THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE.
KOGA BRAGGED TO US
THAT HE WAS THEIR NEW LEADER,
SO MAYBE HE CAUSED AN UPSTART
AND TOOK CONTROL OF THE PACKS BY
USING THE JEWEL SHARDS.
WE BROUGHT MORE FIREWOOD!
- THANK YOU.
WE HAVE PLENTY OF WOOD
FOR THE TIME BEING.
[GRUNTS]
YOU CAN PUT IT
OVER THERE, KAGOME.
BY THE WAY, HAVE YOU SEEN
KIRARA ANYWHERE?
- KIRARA?
I SAW HER WALKING AROUND OUTSIDE
WITH INUYASHA
A LITTLE EARLIER THIS EVENING.
- WITH HIM AGAIN?
SHE'S BEEN FOLLOWING HIM AROUND
CONSTANTLY LATELY.
I WONDER WHY.
- I CANNOT APPROVE OF
YOUR SEEKING THE SHARDS
IN ORDER TO USE THEIR POWER
TO BECOME A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
THAT IS ALL I'M SAYING.
- ARGH! DAMMIT, COME ON.
CONCENTRATE!
ALL RIGHT, I CAN SEE IT--
THE WHIRLPOOL OF DARK ENERGY.
THE FLOW OF
THE DARK ENERGY COLLIDES
AND CREATES THE WIND SCAR.
IF I THRUST TETSUSAIGA
DIRECTLY AT THE WIND SCAR,
I CAN DEFEAT MY ENEMY
WITH ITS TRUE POWER.
HUH!
HOW ABOUT THAT, KIRARA?
PERFECT FORM.
IT'S BEEN GREAT USING YOU
FOR MY TRAINING WITH TETSUSAIGA.
[SNIFFING] I SMELL DINNER.
LET'S GO BACK AND EAT.
[GROWLS]
KIRARA, WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
COME ON. IT'S CHOW TIME!
[WOLVES HOWLING]
- I KNEW IT.
THAT SWORD OF HIS
USES SOME KIND OF WEIRD MAGIC.
DAMMIT! MY FUR'S STILL STANDING
ON END THINKING ABOUT IT.
UGH!
BUT AT LEAST I KNOW
WHAT TO DO NEXT.
- INUYASHA, WATCH OUT!
3 SHARDS!
HE HAS ONE ON HIS RIGHT ARM
AND ONE ON EACH LEG.
- THAT GIRL HAS THE POWER TO SEE
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
I COULD PUT HER SKILLS
TO VERY GOOD USE.
- [SNIFFING]
ALL RIGHT, I'VE PICKED UP
THE SCENT OF THE WOLVES.
I'LL BE ABLE TO LEAD US
RIGHT TO THEM, NO PROBLEM.
- NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT WOULD BE AN INSULT
TO CANINES.
YOU SMELL MUCH WORSE!
- THAT COCKY BASTARD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
HE CALLED ME A MUTT!
[SNIFFING]
- I DON'T BLAME HIM
FOR GETTING UPSET OVER
BEING CALLED A MONGREL,
BUT WHEN
HE'S SNIFFING THE GROUND,
HE SURE LOOKS LIKE ONE.
- I HEARD THAT, SHIPPO.
COME HERE AND SAY THAT.
I DARE YOU!
- WHOA! HE CAN HEAR ME
FROM THAT DISTANCE?
WHAT A BLOODHOUND!
TALK ABOUT CANINE POWER.
- CANINES ARE CARNIVOROUS.
REMEMBER THAT, YOU LITTLE RUNT!
- HMM. DO YOU FEEL THAT?
THERE'S SOMETHING VERY OMINOUS
IN THE AIR.
- SO YOU SENSE SOMETHING, TOO?
KIRARA'S BEEN
VERY RESTLESS LATELY.
- I FEEL A FOREBODING ENERGY
APPROACHING.
IT SEEMS VERY DIFFERENT
FROM THE WOLVES.
- DO YOU THINK
ANOTHER DEMON IS HERE?
[GROWLING]
- IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU GUYS ARRIVED.
CAN YOU FLY ANY SLOWER?
- INUYASHA,
CAN YOU SMELL OR HEAR
ANYTHING UNUSUAL
ABOUT THIS AREA?
- OH, SO I'M YOUR FAITHFUL
TERRIER ALL OF A SUDDEN--
WONDERING IF
I'VE SNIFFED OUT A SCENT
OR HEARD SOMETHING
WITH MY LITTLE DOGGY EARS?
DAMN, YOU GUYS PISS ME OFF--
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU!
- RELAX. I'M SIMPLY ASKING
IF YOU SENSE
ANOTHER PRESENCE IN THE AIR
LIKE WE DO.
[KIRARA GROWLING]
- LOOK, EVERYBODY, UP THERE.
- HMM?
[WOLVES SNARLING AND BARKING]
- AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- SANGO!
- UHH!
[WOLVES WHIMPERING]
- MIROKU. SANGO!
- DAMN THESE WOLVES.
WHAT'S GOING ON UP THERE?
HMM? HEY, WHAT IS THAT?
- SEE YOU LATER, MUTT-FACE.
- INUYASHA!
- AAH!
- NOW SHE'S MINE!
- KAGOME!
UHH!
NO! KAGOME!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- THIS CLIFF IS NOTHING TO ME.
I GOT SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
IN MY LEGS.
- [KAGOME AND SHIPPO
SCREAMING]
- YOU'RE NEVER
GONNA REACH IT! NO!
[SCREAMING]
WE'RE GONNA FALL.
SOMEBODY HELP ME!
- WILL YOU SHUT UP
AND STOP SCREAMING?!
- I'LL SCREAM IF I WANT TO!
[SCREAMING]
- LET GO OF ME! AGH!
UHH!
[GASP] THEY'RE GONNA PAY FOR
WHAT THEY DID.
HUH?
WHERE ARE THEY GOING?
- HA! HE CAN'T KEEP UP
WITH ME.
NO ONE CAN RUN
AS FAST AS I CAN.
- OF COURSE NOT.
YOU HAVE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
JAMMED IN YOUR LEGS.
YOU DON'T GET BRAGGING RIGHTS
IF YOU'RE CHEATING, YOU KNOW.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF NERVE,
KIDNAPPING ME LIKE THAT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- HUMPH.
- YOU SEE THAT?
WAS THAT A BIRD?
TELL ME THAT WAS JUST
A REALLY BIG BIRD.
COME ON, SAY SOMETHING.
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT!
[SNARLING]
WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
- THEY'RE NOT CANARIES,
I CAN TELL YOU THAT MUCH,
AND I BET THEY WANT DINNER.
SEE IF ANY OF THEM HAVE
A JEWEL SHARD.
CAN YOU TELL?
- HUH?
- I KNOW YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO SEE JEWEL SHARDS.
DO THOSE DEMON BIRDS HAVE ANY?
- NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
I DON'T SEE ANY
FROM HERE, ANYWAY.
- TAKE A GOOD LOOK.
NOT EVEN THE ONES
OVER THE CLIFF?
- NO.
- FINE.
THEN I'VE GOT NO USE
FOR THEM.
SEE YA, BUZZARD BRAINS.
WE'RE OUTTA HERE!
- HUH?
HEY, IT'S KOGA!
KOGA'S COME BACK!
- HEY, KOGA!
- [KAGOME GRUNTS]
- HEY, GUYS. I'M BACK.
- [GASP] WHAT'S THIS?
[WOLVES HOWLING]
IT MUST BE THE DEN OF
THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE.
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- OH, MAN,
I REALLY GOT WASHED DOWNRIVER.
- IT SEEMS THAT KOGA'S PLAN WAS
TO KIDNAP KAGOME ALL ALONG.
- SHE'S GONE?
THAT'S WHY THE WOLVES RETREATED.
THEIR MASTER GOT WHAT HE WANTED,
SO THERE WAS NO USE STAYING.
- SO IT WOULD APPEAR.
[KIRARA SNARLING]
SANGO, ANY SIGN OF KAGOME?
- I ALMOST CAUGHT UP WITH THEM,
BUT I RAN INTO
SOME HEAVY INTERFERENCE.
- WITH WHAT?
- WHAT ARE THESE THINGS?
- ARE THEY BIRDS?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT THERE WEREN'T
JUST 10 OR 20 OF THEM.
THEY COVERED THE ENTIRE SKY.
- SO, THESE CREATURES EXPLAIN
THE FOREBODING ENERGY WE SENSED.
- I IMAGINE THESE MOUNTAIN PEAKS
ARE THEIR TERRITORY.
- IF SANGO FOUND
THESE FLYING DEMONS A CHALLENGE,
THEN WE MAY HAVE MORE THAN
JUST THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE
TO WORRY ABOUT.
[SCREAMING]
- HMM?
- THOSE ARE SHIPPO'S
WARNING SIGNS.
THAT'S RIGHT!
- I NOTICED THE LITTLE RUNT
WAS MISSING.
HE MUST HAVE BEEN CAPTURED
WITH KAGOME.
- THEY'RE LEADING STRAIGHT INTO
THOSE MOUNTAINS.
[MUSHROOMS SCREAMING]
- WE'VE GOT NO TIME TO WASTE.
LET'S GO! UHH!
[GRUNTING]
- HEY, KOGA,
WHO'S THE WOMAN?
- [GASP]
THIS PLACE IS FULL OF
MAN-EATING WOLVES AND SKELETONS.
UHH!
- NICE-LOOKING PREY, KOGA.
CAN I HAVE ONE OF THE LEGS?
- I CLAIM FIRST DIBS
ON THE LIVER.
- [GASP]
THEY'RE GONNA EAT ME?!
- THIS WOMAN IS OFF-LIMITS.
I'LL KILL ANYONE
WHO TRIES TO TAKE A BITE.
- [ALL GASP]
- OH, I GET IT.
HE KIDNAPPED ME BECAUSE I CAN
SEE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
SO HE NEEDS ME.
AT LEAST THAT MEANS I'M SAFE
FOR A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
- HUH?
[WOLVES SNIFFING]
OH, YEAH, HIM.
I FORGOT HE GRABBED ONTO MY TAIL
WHEN I CAPTURED THE GIRL.
I ASSUMED HE FELL OFF.
GUESS NOT.
HERE, HAVE AN APPETIZER.
- UHH!
UH-OH.
KAGOME, HELP!
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
DO YOU WANT MY HELP
WITH THE JEWEL SHARDS,
OR DON'T YOU?
IF ANYONE LAYS A HAND ON SHIPPO,
I REFUSE TO HELP!
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU DO TO ME!
- WELL! YOU'VE GOT MORE GUTS
THAN I THOUGHT.
- HUH?
- COME ON, MOVE.
WHOA! YOU GUYS HAVE PACKED ON
A LOT OF WEIGHT AGAIN,
YOU BUNCH OF GLUTTONS.
YOU'RE NOT EATING ANYTHING MORE
FOR THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
HERE YOU GO.
- SHIPPO!
- KAGOME! OHH!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE JUST SAVED SHIPPO.
DON'T TELL ME
THAT GUY'S GOT A NICE SIDE.
- MOVE! MOVE OUT OF THE WAY!
WE'VE GOT INJURED! MAKE ROOM!
- [GRUNTING]
- WHAT HAPPENED OUT THERE?
GET HIM SOME WATER.
COME ON, HURRY UP!
- AHEM.
[GULPING]
- [GROANING]
- WAS IT THEM?
- YEAH. THEY ATTACKED HARD
DURING THE MIDDAY CHANGING
OF THE WATCH.
ONLY THESE TWO
MANAGED TO ESCAPE.
OTHERS FELL OFF THE CLIFF
TO THEIR DEATH
OR WERE CARRIED AWAY.
- SUCH TERRIBLE WOUNDS.
- YOU SAW THEM EARLIER.
THEY CALL THEMSELVES
THE BIRDS OF PARADISE,
BUT THEY'RE OUR ARCHENEMIES,
AND THIS IS DEFINITELY
THEIR DOING.
THEY'RE BRUTAL DEMONS,
AND WE'VE LOST MANY TO THEM.
WITHOUT WARNING,
THEY SWOOP DOWN SILENTLY
AND CAPTURE OUR COMRADES WITH
THEIR SHARP, POWERFUL CLAWS.
- THEN WHAT DO THEY DO?
- THEY EAT THEM.
WE'VE COME ACROSS
THEIR NESTS BEFORE
AND HAVE FOUND THEM LITTERED
WITH HUNDREDS OF WOLF BONES.
- AND EVEN YOU'RE NO MATCH
FOR THEM?
- THAT'S JUST IT.
ONE OF THE BIRDS OF PARADISE
POSSESSES A SACRED JEWEL SHARD,
AND NOW HE'S EVEN FASTER
THAN WE ARE.
A FEW WEEKS AGO, HE KILLED 50
OF OUR WOLVES IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
IT'S GOTTA BE THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
AT THIS RATE,
I'M AFRAID OUR PACKS
WILL BE WIPED OUT COMPLETELY,
SO WE NEED TO RESTORE
THE BALANCE OF POWER SOMEHOW.
- SO YOUR PACK IS IN DANGER,
AND THAT'S WHY
YOU WANT ME TO FIND
WHICH BIRD OF PARADISE
HAS THE SHARD.
- YOU'LL SCOUT OUT
THE BIRD WITH THE SHARD,
AND THEN WE'LL ATTACK ITS NEST
AND STEAL IT FROM HIM.
OTHERWISE, THE FIGHTING
BETWEEN US WILL DRAG ON,
AND LIVES WILL CONTINUE TO
BE SACRIFICED SENSELESSLY.
SO, YOU GONNA HELP US OUT
OR WHAT?
- YES, I WILL.
I'D BETTER COOPERATE.
EITHER I HELP THEM OUT,
OR I'M DOG FOOD.
THE ONLY WAY
I'LL BE ABLE TO ESCAPE ALIVE
AND SEE INUYASHA AGAIN IS TO
HEAD OUT TO BATTLE WITH THEM.
- STRING HIM ALONG
A LITTLE WHILE LONGER, KAGOME.
MY MUSHROOMS ARE LEADING
INUYASHA AND THE OTHERS
STRAIGHT TO US.
- WHAT'S THIS?
CAN YOU EAT THEM?
- HUH? AAH!
- THESE ARE GROSS!
DON'T PICK THEM
IF YOU CAN'T EAT THEM.
[WOLVES GROWLING]
- [GASP] THEY PICKED
ALL MY MUSHROOMS!
- THAT'S THE LAST
OF THE MUSHROOMS.
- OH, MAN,
WHICH WAY DID THEY GO?
SHIPPO'S STUPID TRAIL LED US TO
THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE!
- THE SCENT OF WOLVES
IS ALL OVER THE PLACE,
AND I DON'T HAVE INUYASHA'S
SENSE OF SMELL.
- TELL ME, IS THE WOLF SCENT
OVERPOWERING KAGOME'S,
OR CAN YOU PICK IT UP
FROM HERE?
- [SNIFFING]
[GRUNTS]
- INUYASHA,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I'M STARTING TO SMELL BIRD,
AND I'LL TELL YOU THIS MUCH--
IT AIN'T NO TURKEY DINNER.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR YOU
RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO RESCUE KAGOME,
SO GET OUT OF MY WAY! UHH!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
[VOICE ECHOING]
[GROWLING]
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- THE BATTLE
BETWEEN THE WOLF DEMONS
AND THE BIRDS OF PARADISE
IS ABOUT TO START.
THE DEMON BIRDS SWOOP DOWN
AND ATTACK WITHOUT WARNING.
THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE FIGHTS
FEROCIOUSLY FROM THE CLIFFS,
AND INUYASHA
STILL HASN'T COME.
MEANWHILE, KOGA IS STARTING
TO SAY THINGS
THAT ARE WEIRDING ME OUT.
THIS IS NO TIME TO MAKE
ANY DECLARATIONS OF LOVE.
NEXT ON "INUYASHA"...
SEE YOU SOON!