- A SPIDER ON HIS BACK?
- YES, INUYASHA SAID HE SAW
A SPIDER-SHAPED BURN MARK
IN THE MIDDLE OF
MIROKU'S BACK.
- THE THIEF ONIGUMO
SUFFERED FROM TERRIBLE BURNS.
PERHAPS THAT MEANS
THAT MIROKU IS ONIGUMO.
- A SPIDER ON HIS BACK.
THAT SHALL SERVE AS
MIROKU'S OWN SIGN.
- KIKYO DIDN'T USE
THE POWER OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
TO SAVE HERSELF.
- KIKYO CHOSE DEATH
OVER LIFE.
SHE CHOSE TO FOLLOW INUYASHA.
- THIS MANSION IS ENORMOUS!
WHAT DO YOU THINK MIROKU?
WILL WE BE STAYING
HERE FOR THE NIGHT?
- I'LL WAGER MIROKU TELLS
THE OWNERS AN OMINOUS CLOUD
HANGS OVER THE MANSION.
- YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
I HAVE A LEGITIMATE
REASON FOR COMING HERE.
- SO THESE DEMONS CARRY OFF
THE SOULS OF DEAD GIRLS?
- YES, AS IF LOSING OUR PRINCESS
WASN'T UPSETTING ENOUGH.
I CANNOT HAVE HER SOUL
STOLEN BEFORE IT REACHES
ITS FINAL RESTING PLACE.
- NO SUCH THING WILL OCCUR.
REST ASSURED THAT
MY ASSOCIATES AND I
SHALL PROTECT THE PRINCESSES
SOUL FROM THESE DEMONS.
- HMM?
- WHAT'D I TELL YOU?
SAME OLD LINE, SAME
OLD UNWARRANTED FEAST.
- PERHAPS, BUT ONE NEEDS
A FULL STOMACH IF HE IS
TO HEAD INTO COMBAT.
THIS PLACE IS TOO QUIET.
THE AIR IS THICK WITH EVIL.
- [LAUGHING]
- [HUMMING]
AHH! OH, I FOUND SOME.
KIKYO!
KIKYO, I FOUND SOME!
LOOK, IS THIS A MEDICINAL HERB?
- YES, WELL DONE, SAYO.
IT'S CALLED A LANTERN PLANT,
AND IT'S USED
TO REDUCE SWELLING.
- KIKYO! KIKYO!
HEY, WHAT ARE THESE?
- DO THESE
GRASSES CURE ANYTHING?
- LET'S SEE.
- MASTER SEIKAI,
ARE YOU CERTAIN THAT THE
YOUNG PRIESTESS IS A DEMON?
SHE LOOKS NOTHING MORE
THAN A HUMAN TO MY EYES.
- THEN YOU LACK IN TRAINING.
CAN YOU NOT SENSE IT?
THIS AREA RESONATES
WITH A SINISTER EVIL.
- EXCUSE ME, MONK?
- HUH?
- I SEE YOU HAVE BEEN
WATCHING ME FOR SOME TIME NOW.
- HOW VERY AWKWARD.
YOU PERCEIVED US, DID YOU?
YOUR BEAUTY IS SO REMARKABLE,
I COULD NOT HELP
BUT STARE AT YOU.
- SPARE ME YOUR FLATTERY.
- APPARENTLY MY ETIQUETTE
IS IN SORE NEED OF REFINEMENT.
OHH!
- HMMM.
- GATHER THE SCROLL
FOR ME, WILL YOU?
IT CONTAINS
A SUTRA WARDING OFF EVIL.
SHOULD A DEMON TOUCH IT,
THE BEAST'S TRUE NATURE
WILL BE REVEALED.
- HOW FORTUNATE WE HAVE
SUCH SUTRAS TO PROTECT US.
HERE.
YOUR SCROLL.
- [GASP]
SHE TOUCHED THE SUTRA.
YET, THERE WAS
NO TRANSFORMATION.
AAHHHH!
- NOW, LET US GO, SHALL WE?
- I-I'M NOT
CERTAIN WHAT TRANSPIRED.
A TREMENDOUS FORCE
DID PASS THROUGH MY BODY.
NO, IT'S GONE!
- WHAT IS IT?
WHAT UPSETS YOU, MASTER SEIKAI?
- LOOK AT THE SCROLL.
- HUH?
THE SUTRA HAS DISAPPEARED.
- IT'S AS THOUGH
IT HAS BEEN ERASED.
- HUH?
- PRIESTESS!
I DO NOT KNOW
WHAT BINDS YOU TO THIS WORLD,
BUT IT IS CERTAINLY NOT
A PLACE FOR YOU TO LINGER.
GO, AND RETURN
TO WHERE YOU BELONG!
- WHAT'S HE GOIN' ON ABOUT?
- HE'S A STRANGE MONK.
- THAT WOMAN
IS NO ORDINARY DEMON.
SHE IS MUCH STRONGER
AND MUCH MORE SINISTER.
- LOOK YONDER.
IT'S LADY KIKYO.
- LUCKILY, WE HAVE
SUCH A TALENTED AND KIND
PRIESTESS IN OUR MIDST.
- AYE, SHE CURES OURS AILS
AND CHEERS THE CHILDREN.
- IT IS SO.
WE ARE TRULY BLESSED, INDEED.
- THE WITCH URASUE
DESIRED THE SPIRITUAL
POWER OF A PRIESTESS,
SO SHE ROBBED THE BONES
AND EARTH FROM MY GRAVE
AND FIRED MY BODY IN HER KILN.
THE SOUL THAT HAS TRANSMIGRATED
INTO THIS BODY SUITS ME WELL.
WHY DID YOU BETRAY ME, INUYASHA?
FOR A SECOND TIME,
YOU ASKED ME TO DIE, INUYASHA.
SO, WHY DO YOU LOOK SAD?
IS IT BECAUSE YOU FEEL
THE HEAT FROM MY HAND?
THE HEAT OF ANGER,
THE FLAMES OF VENGEANCE.
- KIKYO!
- KIKYO?
DID YOU HEAR ME?
- SAYO.
- KIKYO, YOU WILL ALWAYS
STAY HERE WITH US, WON'T YOU?
- HMM? HMM...
TELL ME, SAYO,
ARE YOU FOND OF ME?
- MMM-HMM.
- THAT MAKES ME HAPPY.
YOU ARE AS DEAR TO ME AS THOUGH
YOU WERE MY YOUNGER SISTER.
- OHH, TRULY?
- YES.
I CAN LIVE HERE.
I CAN RESIDE IN THIS VILLAGE.
I KNOW I CAN DO IT.
BUT THE QUESTION REMAINS
WILL I BE PERMITTED TO DO IT?
- WELL, EVERYTHING
LOOKS CLEAR OUTSIDE.
ANYTHING UNUSUAL IN HERE?
- NO, SO FAR
EVERYTHING'S BEEN GOOD.
- GOOD--
SO, WHERE'D MIROKU GET TO?
- IT SOUNDS LIKE THERE'S ONE
OTHER PRINCESS LIVING HERE,
SO MIROKU SAID HE WANTED
TO GO MAKE SURE SHE WAS SAFE.
- OH, SURE.
- THE YOUNGER
PRINCESS IS PETRIFIED.
- LEAVE HER--
I MEAN, THINGS--TO ME.
IF SHE IS LIKE HER SISTER,
THE YOUNGER PRINCESS MUST
BE A BEAUTY BEYOND COMPARE.
AHH, I LOVE MY JOB.
- MIROKU, AM I SUPPOSED TO HELP
YOU PROTECT THIS YOUNGER SISTER?
- FIRST WE MUST DO WHAT WE
CAN TO LAY HER FEARS TO REST.
PERHAPS YOU CAN TRANSFORM
INTO SOMETHING CUTE AND FUZZY.
- WHAT FOR?
- A BUNNY.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO SEE ON UP CLOSE!
YOU SEE?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
- I'LL EXPLAIN IT TO YOU ONE
DAY, WHEN YOU'RE OLD ENOUGH
TO TALK MAN TO MAN.
- HE'S SOME PLAYER.
TOO BAD HE HAS
EVERYONE CONVINCED HE'S A SAINT.
OTHERWISE, I'D GIVE
HIM A GOOD STOMPING.
HMMM?
UH, ISN'T THIS
A LITTLE CLOSE, KAGOME?
- DEAL WITH IT.
SHE'S CREEPING ME OUT.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE SHE COULD
SPRING TO LIFE ANY MINUTE NOW.
- HMM? THAT WAS YOUR MOTIVATION?
- WHY ELSE WOULD IT BE?
HEY, GET YOUR MIND
OUT OF THE GUTTER,
AND CONCENTRATE ON WHAT
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE DOING.
- GUTTER?! AS IF!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO JUMPED ME
AND STARTED PRESSING FLESH.
- A-HA! SO YOU DID HAVE
YOUR MIND IN THE TRASH.
- I WAS MINDING MY OWN BUSINESS!
- YOU WERE HITTING ON ME.
- I MUST TAKE LEAVE.
YOUR SISTER'S SOUL REQUIRES
MY UNWAVERING PROTECTION.
- DO NOT ABANDON ME,
MASTER MIROKU!
I FEAR FOR MY SAFETY.
- NO ONE WILL
COME AFTER YOU.
I GUARANTEE IT.
- YOU ARE TOO CRUEL.
- AAAHH!
- TIME TO WORK.
AAARRHHH!
- HER SPIRIT IS SAFE AGAIN.
- YOU THINK IT'S OVER?
NOT LIKELY.
- WAIT,
THERE'S SOMETHING OUTSIDE.
SO, THERE'S MORE THAN
JUST ONE OF THOSE DEMONS.
- LOOK, THEY'RE ALL
CARRYING SPIRITS OF THE DEAD.
- THERE'S SO MANY.
WHERE COULD THEY BE
GOING WITH ALL THOSE SOULS?
- [PANTING]
AFTER THEM!
QUICKLY!
- PLEASE, STAY WITH ME.
- MIROKU HAVING
WOMEN TROUBLES AGAIN?
- I THINK SHE MAY BE
A DEMON AND NOT A WOMAN AT ALL.
- OOHHH! OH, LITTLE FOX,
HOW CAN YOU TREAT ME SO?
[WOLF HOWLING]
[ALL SNORING]
- KIKYO IS
TROUBLED BY SOMETHING.
IT MUST BE WHAT THE MONK
SAID TO HER THIS AFTERNOON.
- I DO NOT KNOW
WHAT BINDS YOU TO THIS WORLD,
BUT IT IS CERTAINLY NOT
A PLACE FOR YOU TO LINGER.
GO, AND RETURN
TO WHERE YOU BELONG!
- [WHIMPERING]
AHHH, I CAN'T SLEEP.
HUH?
KIKYO'S OUTSIDE.
HMMM.
WHERE COULD SHE BE
GOING AT THIS TIME OF NIGHT?
SHE SAID SOMETHING
RATHER PECULIAR TODAY.
I HOPE SHE WILL NOT
LEAVE OUR VILLAGE FOR ELSEWHERE.
[GASP]
- COME AND ALLOW ME TO LEAD YOU,
THE TRAGIC SOULS OF MAIDENS.
- KIKYO IS
CONTROLLING THE LOST SOULS.
- ARE YOU UNABLE TO CROSS OVER?
YOU ARE DEAD, YOUNG PRIESTESS.
YOU MUST NOW
PASS TO THE NETHER WORLD.
- WOULD YOU NOT
OVERLOOK MY PRESENCE HERE?
I MERELY WISH TO LIVE
IN PEACE IN A SMALL VILLAGE.
- IF YOU WISH TO LIVE IN PEACE,
THEN WHY MUST YOU
GATHER SOULS OF THE DEAD?
- I HAVE REASONS.
- YOU REQUIRE
THOSE SOULS IN ORDER TO
SUSTAIN THAT BODY OF YOURS.
- WHAT ACTION WILL YOU TAKE?
I TAKE IT YOU WON'T LEAVE.
- I WILL SEND YOU
WHERE YOU BELONG.
I SHALL DO IT FOR YOUR SAKE.
- UGH!
- YOU CANNOT ESCAPE THIS
DEMON-BINDING SPELL OF MINE!
I SHALL EXTINGUISH YOUR LIGHT
AND SAVE YOUR SOUL
FROM ETERNAL MISERY!
- SAVE ME?
A WRETCH SUCH AS YOU
PRESUMES TO SAVE MY SOUL?
- OOOHHH!
- AAHHH...AAAAAHHH!
- YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN
BETTER TO LEAVE ME BE
AND NOT END YOUR LIFE.
- PRIESTESS, TELL ME
WHAT YOUR PURPOSE IS.
TIME CONTINUES FOR THE LIVING.
THEY CARVE THEIR FUTURES
WITH EACH PASSING MOMENT.
HOWEVER, FOR THE DEAD, SUCH AS
YOURSELF, TIME STANDS STILL.
THUS, THE DEAD AND THE
LIVING CANNOT RESIDE TOGETHER.
AND YET YOU INSIST ON TRYING.
HOW TRAGIC.
- TRAGIC, YOU SAY?
I AM TRAGIC?
UH...
WHO GOES?
- [WHIMPERING]
- SAYO.
WERE YOU--
DID YOU WITNESS THAT?
- [WHIMPERING]
- SAYO...
FORGIVE ME.
I DID NOT MEAN
FOR YOU TO SEE SUCH A SIGHT.
- WAIT, KIKYO!
- FAREWELL, SAYO.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- COME ON!
WE HAVE TO SAVE THE SOULS
OF THOSE LOST WOMEN!
- WHERE DO YOU WANT US TO GO?
- OH, YEAH. GOOD QUESTION.
- THE DEMON'S
DISAPPEARED WITHOUT A TRACE.
WE WOULDN'T KNOW
WHERE TO START SEARCHING.
- AND THERE'S CERTAINLY
NO POINT IN RETURNING TO
THE MANSION, IS THERE?
- I BELIEVE YOU HAVE OTHER
REASONS FOR THAT OPINION,
AS IN A CERTAIN PRINCESS
WHOSE FONDNESS OF YOU IS
A LITTLE TOO OBVIOUS.
- [COUGHS]
- [SLURPING]
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
ARE YOU GETTING LAZY
IN YOUR OLD AGE OR SOMETHING?
- I'M JUST NOT
ESPECIALLY INTERESTED.
I MEAN, WHAT'S IN IT FOR US?
IT'S NOT AS THOUGH
WE'LL FIND A JEWEL FRAGMENT.
- I SHOULD HAVE
SEEN THAT ONE COMING.
COME ON, JUST ONE
ON THE HOUSE FOR US HUMANS.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M TIRED OF--
HELPING PEOPLE ALL THE TIME.
LOOK, I'M GONNA BE
A GREAT DEMON SOMEDAY,
SO WHY SHOULD I WASTE MY TIME
GOING AROUND RESCUING HUMANS?
- OH, AREN'T YOU THE VILLAIN?
YOU'RE PRACTICALLY
A SAINT, AND YOU KNOW IT.
- SAINT? OK, WHERE ARE YOU
GOING WITH THIS ONE, KAGOME?
- IT'S SUPPOSED
TO BE A COMPLIMENT.
- HUH! LOOK, I'M STILL NOT
INTERESTED IN HELPING THEM,
SO COUNT ME OUT.
YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
I'M STILL TALKING HERE!
- LOOK!
- AN OCTOPUS.
- MORE LIKE A HUMAN.
- DO SOMETHING!
MOVE IT! HURRY!
- WHY DO I--AAH!
- LOOK TO THE SAINT INSIDE YOU!
- THANKFULLY, THE MONK IS ONLY
UNCONSCIOUS AND NOT DROWNED.
- SOUNDS LIKE HE'S COMING TO.
- [GROANING SOFTLY]
- AAH! AH! AH!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU SCARED THE WITS OUT OF ME!
- WHAT IS IT
THAT CAUSES YOU SUCH FRIGHT?
- A DEMON?
- CORRECT.
- YOU'RE SAYING THAT KAGOME
RESEMBLED THIS DEMON YOU SAW?
- AT FIRST GLANCE,
SHE APPEARED TO BE A HUMAN,
BUT CLEARLY SHE WAS
A POSSESSED DEMON...
AND A PRIESTESS.
- A PRIESTESS?
AND SHE LOOKED LIKE ME?
- SH-SHE WAS ABLE
TO WARD OFF MY MASTER'S
IMMENSE SPIRITUAL POWERS.
WAIT, I BELIEVE
I HEARD HER NAME SPOKEN.
IT WAS...KIKYO.
- HUH?
IF I FIND OUT
YOU'RE MAKING THIS UP,
YOU'LL WISH YOU WERE
STILL IN THE RIVER.
- I SPEAK ONLY THE TRUTH!
THE WOMAN LURED AWAY
THE LONELY SOULS OF DEAD WOMEN.
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT!
IT'S HER NAME!
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE
HER NAME IS KIKYO?
- THE CHILDREN
OF THE VILLAGE CALLED HER SO.
I'M CERTAIN.
THE YOUNGSTERS
CALLED HER BY THE NAME KIKYO.
- SO KIKYO WAS THE ONE
RESPONSIBLE FOR LURING AWAY
THE SOULS OF THE DEAD WOMEN?
- [WHIMPERING]
- KIKYO, ARE YOU STILL
IN THE LAND OF THE LIVING?
HOW DID SHE SURVIVE
THE FALL FROM THE CLIFF?
IF SHE IS STILL ALIVE,
IF SHE STILL
WANDERS THE EARTH...
KIKYO, I'LL SAVE YOU.
- DO YOU THINK WE WERE MISTAKEN
IN ALLOWING INUYASHA
TO GO ON HIS OWN?
- HE SURE TOOK OFF IN A HURRY
WHEN HE HEARD THE MONK'S STORY.
- THINK ABOUT IT:
INUYASHA'S PROBABLY
STILL IN LOVE WITH KIKYO.
- WHAT?
- THAT'S WHY IT'S
BETTER TO LEAVE THEM ALONE.
- WHY? WHAT DO THEY
NEED TO BE ALONE FOR?
- I BELIEVE
I UNDERSTAND HER MEANING.
- HUH?
- THE WOMAN HE ONCE LOVED
SO COMPLETELY MAY HAVE CHANGED,
AND IF THAT
WERE INDEED THE CASE,
HE COULD NOT ALLOW OTHERS
TO WITNESS THE CHANGE IN HER
OR IN HIMSELF.
- BUT WHY WOULD THAT BE?
AND COME ON, WHO'S TO SAY?
SHE MIGHT HAVE
CHANGED FOR THE BETTER.
THEN WHAT DO YOU
THINK WOULD HAPPEN?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT ALL WE CAN DO
IS WISH HIM OUR BEST.
- HUH?
- YEAH?
SO THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
- THIS IS DIFFERENT.
IS IT MY IMAGINATION,
OR DID SHE JUST GIVE ME
A REALLY COLD STARE?
- NO, DEFINITELY
NOT YOUR IMAGINATION.
- WHAT DOES
INUYASHA THINK HE'S DOING,
CHASING AFTER KIKYO AGAIN?
- JUST A MOMENT, KAGOME.
- NOW WHAT?!
- I SUPPOSE WE COULD
ALWAYS FOLLOW AFTER INUYASHA.
- NO! I'M NOT CHASING HIM!
THE SKY.
- [GASP]
- OVER THERE!
- THE SAME TYPE OF DEMON!
- AFTER IT!
- GOOD PLAN.
[PANTING]
- AAH!
[GROANING]
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- IT SEEMS LIKE SOMEONE
HAS SEALED THIS AREA OFF.
- SO WE CAN'T PASS?
- RIGHT.
- WAIT, WHERE'S KAGOME?
WHAT HAPPENED TO KAGOME?
[PANTING]
- AH! AH!
BETTER SLOW DOWN.
THE GRASS
IS REALLY SLIPPERY HERE.
HUH? OH, NO,
I MUST HAVE LOST THEM.
[SCREAMING]
MY BACK.
WHERE AM I?
[GASP]
KIKYO!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- KIKYO LIVES.
AN EVIL WITCH
HAD TRIED TO STEAL HER SOUL
BUT ONLY SUCCEEDED
IN REVIVING IT.
AND NOW KIKYO'S SOUL
WANDERS THE LAND OF THE LIVING.
HER BODY IS MADE OF CLAY
AND HOLDS NO WARMTH.
HER EYES ARE COLD AND DARK.
RUN, INUYASHA!
KIKYO IS TRYING TO HURT YOU!
DON'T DO IT, KIKYO.
INUYASHA'S NOT YOUR ENEMY.
NEXT TIME, "KAGOME'S VOICE
AND KIKYO'S KISS."
SEE YOU SOON!