>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSAIGA.
>> WE FACE ANOTHER ATTACK FROM
THE LEGENDARY SPECTERS OF THE
BAND OF SEVEN.
WHAT'S THEIR CONNECTION WITH
KOHAKU, SANGO'S LOST BROTHER,
WHO'S UNDER NARAKU'S CONTROL?
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE, "INUYASHA."
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[CAWING]
>> SO, KYOKOTSU'S DEAD, IS HE?
>> YES, MASTER JAKOTSU.
>> SERVES HIM RIGHT, THE STUPID
FOOL.
GUESS IT'S NO REAL SURPRISE.
HE WAS THE WEAKEST ONE AMONG US,
THAT'S FOR CERTAIN.
SO, TELL ME SOMETHING, KOHAKU.
>> YES?
>> THIS INUYASHA I'M SUPPOSED TO
BE AFTER.
YOU'VE SPENT A GOOD DEAL OF TIME
WITH HIM?
IS HE HANDSOME?
GOOD-LOOKING?
>> I WOULDN'T KNOW.
THAT'S THE KIND OF THING ONLY
YOU CAN DECIDE.
[SIGH]
>> I CAN'T WAIT.
INUYASHA.
I WONDER WHAT COLOR YOUR BLOOD
IS.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
>> HMM?
INUYASHA.
>> LOOK.
>> WARRIORS OFF TO ANOTHER
BATTLE.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
I DIDN'T SENSE ANY KIND OF
UPRISING AROUND HERE.
>> MAYBE THEY'RE GOING TO SUBDUE
SOME DEMONS OR TROUBLEMAKERS.
>> LOOK AT THEM ALL GEARED UP.
TALK ABOUT OVERKILL.
[PANTING]
>> THAT WAS TERRIFYING.
I THOUGHT WE WERE DOOMED.
>> HEAR ME!
THAT WAS PUNISHMENT FROM BUDDHA.
NOW THERE'S NO DENYING THE FEAR
THAT EXISTS DEEP IN YOUR HEART.
>> UH, MASTER?
WHAT'S THAT?
THERE'S A MOUNTAIN TEMPLE UP
AHEAD.
THIS IS HEAVEN-SENT GIFT.
A VERITABLE HEAVEN AND HELL.
>> ENOUGH.
YOU HAVE A WEAK HEART AND YOU
DEPEND TOO HEAVILY ON THE HELP
OF OTHERS, WHICH IS WHY YOU SEE
SUCH ILLUSIONS.
>> YES, SIR.
>> NOW THEN, LET US SEEK
SHELTER.
>> SOUNDS LIKE I'M NOT THE ONLY
ONE WHO DEPENDS ON OTHERS.
>> I HEARD THAT THE BORDER
PATROL WAS TOTALLY ANNIHILATED.
>> IT WAS TERRIBLE, I HEAR.
NO WAY A MAN COULD HAVE DONE IT.
>> ARE THE RUMORS TRUE?
THAT THE PHANTOMS OF THE BAND OF
SEVEN MOUND HAVE BEEN
RESURRECTED?
>> PHANTOMS FROM THE SEVEN MAN
MOUND?
>> EXCUSE ME, GENTLEMEN.
CAN I SPEAK TO YOU FOR A MOMENT?
>> HUMPH.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
>> CAN'T PASS THROUGH WITHOUT
FINDING OUT WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> WELL, THERE IS A TEMPLE
AROUND HERE THAT WAS BUILT TO
QUIET THE SOULS OF THE BAND OF
SEVEN.
>> AND WHAT IS THE BAND OF
SEVEN?
>> THEIR STORY STARTED OVER A
DECADE AGO.
IT IS BELIEVED THEY TRAVELED TO
OUR TERRITORY FROM SOMEWHERE IN
THE EAST.
>> THEY WERE RUTHLESS
MERCENARIES.
THE WHOLE BAND OF THEM.
THEY SERVED NO ONE LORD.
INSTEAD, THEY LIVED AS RONIN,
FINDING TEMPORARY EMPLOYMENT IN
ANY BATTLE THEY HAPPENED TO COME
ACROSS.
>> THERE WERE ONLY 7 OF THEM,
BUT THEIR STRENGTH WAS
INCREDIBLE.
THEY COULD DO THE WORK OF 100
MEN, AND THEIR RAIDS WERE
UNNECESSARILY SAVAGE.
THOSE WHO WERE SLAIN BY THE BAND
OF SEVEN WERE SLICED TO PIECES
AND BURNED ALIVE.
[SHUDDER]
>> THE ONLY PEOPLE CAPABLE OF
SUCH ATROCITIES ARE THOSE WITH A
REAL PENCHANT FOR MURDER.
>> YEAH.
>> THE WARLORDS SOON HAD SECOND
THOUGHTS ABOUT THE MERCENARIES,
WHOSE STRENGTH THEY NOW FEARED.
SO THEY SOLD THEM OUT AND
ORDERED THEM HUNTED DOWN.
[SHOUTING]
IT'S SAID THE MERCENARIES PUT UP
A HARD FIGHT, BUT IT WAS ALL IN
VAIN.
>> I WOULD THINK SO.
>> THE BAND OF SEVEN ESCAPED
INTO THE MOUNTAINS, BUT THEY
WERE COMPLETELY OUTNUMBERED BY
THE WARLORDS' SOLDIERS, WHO
CAME AFTER THEM.
THEY WERE FINALLY CAPTURED JUST
A LITTLE NORTH OF HERE.
THEY WERE EACH BEHEADED, THEN
THEIR BODIES WERE BURIED.
STILL, THE VILLAGERS FEARED
THEIR CURSE AND DECIDED TO QUIET
THE 7 SOULS.
EVENTUALLY, THEY ERECTED A TOMB
AT THE BASE OF THE SACRED
MOUNTAIN.
THE TOMB OF THE BAND OF SEVEN.
>> I SEE.
>> WE OVERHEARD YOU TALK ABOUT
THEIR SPIRITS BEING RESURRECTED.
[OLD MEN GRUMBLE]
>> IT'S TRUE.
THEY SAY THAT THE TOMBSTONE
SPLIT INTO TWO.
AND THERE WAS NO LIGHTNING THAT
DAY, EITHER.
>> IT'S BELIEVED THAT THE 7
SOULS ESCAPED.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
>> IT'S TRUE.
>> HMM.
WANDERING SPIRITS.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE
VILLAGERS' TALE, MIROKU?
>> IT'S POSSIBLE THAT WITH
NARAKU'S EVIL GONE FROM HERE,
ALL THE RABBLE HAVE BECOME FREE
AND POSSIBLY EVEN RESURRECTED.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHETHER THEY'RE
SUPPOSED TO BE SPECTERS OR
DEMONS.
WE'RE WALKING IN THAT DIRECTION,
THOUGH, SO WE'RE BOUND TO FIND
OUT.
IF WE COME ACROSS 'EM, WE JUST
KILL 'EM.
>> HUH?
>> HMM?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAGOME?
>> I SENSE A SECRET JEWEL SHARD
AROUND HERE.
HUH?
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, KILALA?
>> WHAT'S WITH HER?
SHE'S SURE ACTING STRANGE.
>> HUH?
SANGO.
>> UHH!
>> SANGO.
>> KILALA, WAS IT KOHAKU'S
PRESENCE THAT YOU SENSED?
[KILALA GROWLS]
HE MUST BE SOMEWHERE ON THIS
MOUNTAIN.
HUH?
THE SAIMYOUSHOU.
HMM.
KOHAKU!
>> I WANTED TO FORGET IT, BUT IT
WOULDN'T GO AWAY.
I KEPT SEEING HER FACE.
>> KOHAKU.
[BUZZING]
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> IT'S NARAKU.
YOU'RE STILL UNDER HIS SPELL.
>> WHY?
WHY DO I REMEMBER YOUR FACE?
OH...
[GRUNTING]
>> DON'T RUSH IT.
IT'LL TAKE TIME TO REMEMBER.
WE'LL BE TOGETHER FROM NOW ON,
KOHAKU.
>> UM, EXCUSE ME.
[BUZZING]
>> KOHAKU!
>> UNH!
UHH!
>> NO! STOP!
>> DIE.
>> KOHAKU, YOU'VE GOT TO TRY AND
WAKE UP.
KOHAKU!
UNH!
[WHIMPER]
>> HMM?
>> KOHAKU!
KILALA.
WHAT IS THAT?
BROTHER.
>> YOU SHOULDN'T BE SO CARELESS.
YOU'RE BEING WATCHED.
[BUZZING]
>> HA HA HA!
YOU WERE TAKING FAR TOO LONG, SO
WE CAME INSTEAD.
HA!
THAT WOMAN.
YOU KNOW HER?
[HORSES NEIGHING]
>> HMM?
HEY, YOU THERE!
MAKE WAY AND GET OFF THE PATH AT
ONCE!
>> HUH?
>> MEN, STOP YOUR HORSES!
[GRUNTING]
>> DID YOU SAY SOMETHING TO ME,
WARRIOR?
>> WHAT MANNER OF BEING ARE YOU?
YOUR APPEARANCE IS STRANGE.
>> YOU BETTER BE CAREFUL IF
YOU'RE GOING ON AHEAD.
I HEAR A FRIGHTENING SPECTER IS
IN THE AREA.
>> SPARE US YOUR WARNING,
STRANGER.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY TO SLAY IT.
>> HA HA HA!
I ASSUME YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
THE SPECTER LOOKS LIKE, DO YOU?
>> MEANING WHAT?
DO YOU KNOW ITS APPEARANCE?
[JAKOTSU CHUCKLING]
OF COURSE I DO, FOR I AM THE
PHANTOM YOU SEEK.
[GASPING]
>> GUN BATTALION, TO THE FRONT!
>> OH, WHAT ARE THOSE?
>> A SPECTER OVER A DECADE OLD
WOULDN'T BE FAMILIAR WITH THIS
NEW KIND OF WEAPON.
FIRE!
>> UHH!
[GUNFIRE]
>> HUH?
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
WHAT WERE THOSE STRANGE POPPING
SOUNDS?
>> I THINK I KNOW.
IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN GUNFIRE.
>> HMM?
GUNFIRE?
>> OHH...
HMM.
NOW I UNDERSTAND.
THIS IS THE MATCHLOCK GUN I'VE
HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT.
>> WRETCHED SPIRIT!
SECOND BATTALION, TO THE FRONT!
>> UHH!
>> DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE GOING TO
TRY THAT AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT.
IF IT'S A FIGHT YOU WANT...
FINE!
>> AAH!
>> HUH?
>> THE SMELL OF HUMAN BLOOD.
>> YEAH, AND NOT JUST FROM A
HANDFUL OF PEOPLE, EITHER.
UNH!
>> IMPOSSIBLE!
HOW COULD HE HAVE SLAIN SO MANY
MEN FROM THAT DISTANCE?
>> THIS BRINGS BACK SUCH FOND
MEMORIES OF THE PAST.
>> UNH!
GET HOLD OF YOURSELVES!
DO NOT FEAR HIM!
SURROUND THE PHANTOM!
>> HE'S USING SOME KIND OF
MAGIC!
>> HA HA HA.
NICE TRY, BUT I DON'T USE ANY
SUCH THING.
I DIDN'T THEN, AND I DON'T NOW!
>> THIS SCENT--IT'S WEAK, BUT SO
FAMILIAR.
THAT'S IT.
THE SMELL OF GRAVEYARD SOIL.
HUH?
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
DO YOU SEE ANYTHING?
>> STAY BACK!
>> HUH?
[GASP]
>> THIS IS UNUSUAL.
I'LL TAKE IT BACK TO BROTHER
RENKOTSU.
>> THOSE WERE THE WARRIORS WE
SPOTTED AT THE CROSSROADS.
>> THEY WERE SLAIN BY THAT ONE
PERSON?
>> HUH?
HMM?
[GASP]
ARE YOU THE ONE I'M SEARCHING
FOR?
ARE YOU INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
>> I'VE NEVER MET YOU BEFORE.
HOW'D YOU KNOW MY NAME?
>> YOU'RE ADORABLE!
>> WHAT?
>> HMM.
>> I ESPECIALLY LOVE THOSE FUZZY
EARS OF YOURS.
I WANT THEM.
>> WHO IS HE?
WHAT DOES HE WANT?
JUST WHO ARE YOU, AND WHAT ARE
YOU AFTER?
YOU DON'T SMELL LIKE A LIVING
PERSON.
YOU REEK LIKE CORPSES AND
GRAVEYARD SOIL.
>> UHH...
[SIGH]
>> INUYASHA, COULD HE BE...?
>> YEAH.
SOME VILLAGERS WERE TALKING.
THEY SAID SOME DISGUSTING
SPECTER ROSE UP FROM THE GRAVE.
THAT'D BE YOU, I PRESUME.
>> THEY TOLD US OF A GROUP OF 7
MERCENARIES WHO LOVED TO KILL,
WHO WERE SO EVIL THEY WERE LATER
HUNTED DOWN AND BEHEADED.
ARE YOU ONE OF THE BAND OF 7?
ANSWER ME!
>> INUYASHA IS HANDSOME, BUT
YOU'RE PRETTY SEXY YOURSELF,
MONK.
>> NOBODY MINDS IF I SUCK HIM
UP, DO THEY?
>> NO.
>> HUH?
>> HOLD ON!
HE HAS A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> HUH?
>> MAYBE HE REVIVED THROUGH THE
POWER OF THE SHARD.
>> MAKES SENSE.
WHO GAVE YOU THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARD?
>> HMM.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE CUTE WHEN
YOU'RE ANGRY.
>> SHUT UP!
OK, DEAD MAN!
START TALKING TO ME, AND I WANT
ALL THE DETAILS.
>> OH.
THAT'S AN INTERESTING SWORD YOU
HAVE, INUYASHA.
WHICH IS STRONGER, THOUGH?
MY SWORD OR YOURS?
>> HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> GET BACK, YOU TWO.
IT'S SOME KIND OF TRICK SWORD.
>> HA HA HA.
>> I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
STRANGE ABOUT HIM.
THOSE SOLDIERS LOOKED AWFULLY
WEIRD FOR BEING DEAD.
HE GOT ME THE FIRST TIME.
HE DIDN'T EVEN GIVE ME A CHANCE
TO BLOCK HIS ATTACK.
I FIGURED THERE'D BE SOMETHING
TRICKY ABOUT HIS ASSAULT.
THOSE SOLDIERS DIDN'T EVEN HAVE
A CHANCE TO ATTACK.
IT'S HIS SWORD.
[GRUNTING]
UNH!
UGH!
[GASP]
>> INUYASHA!
>> IT'S A BENDING SWORD!
>> SO TELL ME, INUYASHA.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF JAKOTSU OF
THE BAND OF SEVEN, HUH?
>> NOT TOO MUCH!
UNH!
>> AAH!
>> UNH!
HUH?
>> IT COMES RIGHT BACK EVEN IF
HE REPELS IT.
>> IT'S LIKE A SNAKE.
IT KEEPS STRIKING.
>> UNH!
UNH!
>> KEEP RUNNING.
>> DAMN.
>> GOTCHA.
>> YAH!
UNH!
>> AAH!
ISN'T THIS FUN?
>> UNH!
>> HA HA HA!
>> DAMN, I CAN'T TELL WHERE THE
SWORD WILL COME FROM NEXT.
>> AH, EXCELLENT.
THE FEAR ON YOUR FACE IS SO
EXCITING.
MORE FEAR!
>> HIRIKOSTSU!
>> INUYASHA!
>> SANGO!
>> INUYASHA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I'M FINE.
>> THAT WENCH.
AAH!
UNH!
>> AAH!
AAH!
>> STAY OUT OF THIS, YOU VILE,
DESPICABLE WOMAN.
NO ONE INTERFERES WITH ME AND
INUYASHA!
HUH?
AAH!
>> I'M SICK OF LISTENING TO YOUR
POINTLESS BABBLE!
>> UNH!
OH.
OH, BOY.
THAT WAS CRUEL.
>> OH, GET OVER IT AND TELL ME
WHO GAVE YOU THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARD BEFORE I HAVE TO SERIOUSLY
HURT YOU.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> SANGO, YOU'RE BLEEDING!
>> IT'S JUST A GRAZE.
BUT SOMETHING TELLS ME THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARD WAS PROBABLY
FROM NARAKU.
>> HUH?
>> EARLIER, WHEN I SENSED THE
SACRED JEWEL, IT WAS KOHAKU.
>> HUH?
>> I SAW THE SAIMYOUSHOU NEARBY
HIM AS WELL.
>> MEANING YOUR BROTHER IS STILL
UNDER NARAKU'S SPELL.
>> MM-HMM.
>> OH, SANGO.
[INUYASHA GROWLING]
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> FILTHY VERMIN.
>> EXCELLENT.
HE'S AT IT AGAIN.
JAKOTSU HASN'T CHANGED ONE BIT.
HA HA HA!
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> THIS IS BAD.
I'VE BEEN POISONED, AND I CAN'T
MOVE.
WHAT'S HE PLANNING TO DO WITH
ME?
>> NO ONE CAN BREAK THROUGH MY
POISON BARRIER.
YOU'RE ALL MINE.
I'M SO BLESSED TO HAVE SUCH AN
ADORABLE GIRL TO MYSELF.
I'M NOT PERFECT, BUT YOU'LL GROW
TO LOVE ME.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY OUT OF
HERE.
NEXT TIME, "THE STEALTHY POISON
MASTER, MUKOTSU."
HUH?
SESSHOMARU, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE?