- HMM?
HUH?
AII-YAH!
- WHO ARE YE?
[SHOUTING]
- UHH!
[GRUNTING]
[SHOUTING]
- YOU MEN ATTEND TO HIM.
- I AM CERTAIN THIS IS IT.
AT LAST I HAVE FOUND
HER RESTING SITE.
JUST ENOUGH MOISTURE,
AND THE SOIL IS PERFECT.
- INTRUDER!
WHAT BUSINESS HAVE YE HERE?
IDENTIFY THYSELF.
ANSWER AT ONCE.
- SILENCE, FOOLS!
MY ONLY BUSINESS
LIES WITH THIS GRAVESITE.
ONCE I HAVE THESE ASHES
IN MY POSSESSION,
I SHALL LEAVE
THIS MISERABLE VILLAGE.
- SHE MUST BE AFTER
KIKYO'S REMAINS.
- YAH!
- LEAVE OUR VILLAGE AT ONCE,
OR WE SHALL HAVE NO COURSE
BUT TO STRIKE.
- PERSISTENT WRETCH.
YOU HAVE DONE WELL
NOT TO CROSS MY PATH!
[SCREECHING]
[SCREAMING]
NOW YOU SHALL PAY
FOR YOUR MEDDLING.
[SHOUTING]
- OHH!
- ARE YOU INJURED?
- AAH!
- NO!
DIG NOT MY SISTER'S ASHES!
[GRUNTING]
- I AM THE PRIESTESS KAEDE.
I SHALL NOT ALLOW YE
TO TAKE THOSE REMAINS!
[LAUGHING SOFTLY]
- YOUR THREATS
FALL ON DEAF EARS.
THESE REMAINS NOW BELONG TO ME,
THE DEMON URASUE!
[LAUGHS]
- INUYASHA?
- HUH?
- UHH!
UHH!
I'M STRUCK.
WHO HAS DONE THIS TO ME?
IS THAT KAGOME?
NO, IT ISN'T HER.
IT'S KIKYO, THE WOMAN
WHOSE SPELL PINNED ME TO A TREE.
UHH!
UHH.
IT WAS A DREAM.
I COULD'VE DONE WITHOUT
THOSE NASTY MEMORIES.
[SOFT BREATHING]
KAGOME IS ALMOST IDENTICAL
TO KIKYO.
NO WONDER I HAD THEM CONFUSED
IN MY DREAM.
- HMM?
UHH!
- HUH?
[YAWN]
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
ANYBODY ELSE HOT HERE?
SO, DO YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT SOMETHING?
[GRR]
- AHEM.
- OOPS, DID I SLAP YOU AGAIN?
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- I WAS WRONG.
YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE HER.
- LOOK LIKE WHO?
- YOU'RE NOT EVEN
REMOTELY SIMILAR!
- REMOTELY SIMILAR TO WHO?
- HUH? UH.
HMM.
- HUH?
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
- FORGET IT.
IT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
- HMM?
- WHAT IS THAT?
- DON'T KNOW.
A DEMON?
- I'M PICKING UP THE SMELL
OF FRESH BLOOD.
WAIT! I RECOGNIZE THAT SCENT.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- COME ON, INUYASHA.
HOW ABOUT A HINT AT LEAST?
- UHH.
- WHY THE SUDDEN URGE
TO GO BACK TO THE VILLAGE?
- OH, IT'S A RUSH.
[YAWNS]
- UHH. UHH.
UHH.
- LADY KAEDE,
YOU MUSTN'T MOVE AS OF YET.
- PAY NO MIND.
THESE ARE BUT FLESH WOUNDS.
- KAEDE!
- HMM?
YOU'RE BACK!
- WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- UHH.
HMPH.
WHAT, YOU STILL ALIVE?
TRUST A STUBBORN
OLD GOAT LIKE YOU
TO REFUSE TO GIVE INJURIES
TIME TO HEAL.
- THIS IS NOTHING.
- SO YOU PICKED UP
THE SCENT OF MY BLOOD
AS A SPECTER PASSED, DID YOU?
- DON'T CHANGE THE SUBJECT
ON ME.
SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE
AND TAKE IT EASY!
- I GET IT.
HE WANTED TO COME BACK
TO THE VILLAGE
BECAUSE HE SMELLED YOUR BLOOD
AND WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
[SHRIEKING]
- WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
- THE SPECTER.
SHE DESECRATED
MY SISTER KIKYO'S GRAVESITE.
- THIS WAS HER TOMB?
- YES, AND I WAS VIRTUALLY
POWERLESS TO STOP THE ASSAULT.
- THESE REMAINS
NOW BELONG TO ME,
THE DEMON URASUE.
[LAUGHS]
- MY SISTER HAD
UNUSUALLY STRONG POWERS,
EVEN FOR A PRIESTESS,
AS SHE WAS.
HER REMAINS HAVE FALLEN
INTO THE HANDS OF EVIL.
WHO KNOWS TO WHAT END
KIKYO'S POWERS
WILL BE EXPLOITED?
INUYASHA.
- YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
APPARENTLY YOU'VE FORGOTTEN
KIKYO BETRAYED ME.
I AM NOT SO LUCKY.
I CAN STILL REMEMBER THE PAIN
FROM THE ARROW SHE USED
TO PIERCE MY CHEST.
- MMM.
FORGIVE ME.
- IT HAPPENED 50 YEARS AGO,
BUT TO INUYASHA,
THE MEMORY STILL SEEMS FRESH.
- IT'S INUYASHA!
[SHOUTING]
- BEING THE HALF-DEMON
THAT HE WAS,
INUYASHA WANTED TO TAKE
THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL
TO ENABLE HIM TO BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
- HMM.
- WHEN HE CAME TO THE VILLAGE
AND STOLE THE JEWEL,
THE PRIESTESS KIKYO
SHOT A SACRED ARROW,
WHICH HELD HIM FAST TO A TREE.
- UHH!
[SHOUTING]
- HMM?
- UHH!
HA.
SO THERE.
FINALLY, A WAY FOR ME
TO BECOME ALL-DEMON AT LAST.
HUH!
UHH!
- INUYASHA!
- UHH!
UHH--OOH--UUH!
KI--KIKYO.
UHH.
I THOUGHT WE...
[MOANING]
- IN A TRAGIC TWIST OF FATE,
KIKYO LOST HER LIFE
IN THE BATTLE.
- SISTER KIKYO!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- HMM.
THE DEMON URASUE.
SHE STOLE MORE THAN
SIMPLY KIKYO'S ASHES.
I ALSO SMELLED THE STRONG SCENT
OF FRESH SOIL AS SHE PASSED,
SOIL FROM THE GRAVESITE.
WHAT COULD SHE BE SCHEMING?
HMM?
- THERE YOU ARE.
LET'S GO.
- HMPH.
WHERE TO?
- COME ON.
DON'T YOU FEEL A BIT SORRY
FOR KIKYO?
HER GRAVE WAS VIOLATED.
I KNOW YOU WERE BETRAYED BY HER,
BUT THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
IT'S BEEN AT LEAST 50 YEARS
SINCE SHE PASSED AWAY.
- HMM.
- HMM?
HMM.
- HUH! WATCH THE HAIR!
- MIND EXPLAINING WHY
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO LOOK ME STRAIGHT IN THE EYE
SINCE YESTERDAY?
[GULP]
- HMM.
YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY
IMAGINING THINGS.
- I GET IT!
THIS IS ALL ABOUT ME
LOOKING LIKE KIKYO.
THAT'S IT, ISN'T IT?
THAT'S WHY YOU CAN'T LOOK AT ME!
[GASP]
INUYASHA!
- IT'S NOT...
[SIGH]
- HUH?
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
- UH...WHAT'S HE DOING?
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
HOLD THE PHONE!
- AAH!
UHH!
- HEH HEH.
OH...
OK, NOW I'M OFFICIALLY FREAKED.
OH...WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE ALMOST KISSED ME!
[GRUNTING]
- CAN WE LOSE
SOME OF THE VIOLENCE?
- SURE, AS SOON AS YOU STOP
ACTING SO WEIRD.
- YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S BEING A LUNATIC!
- HMM?
- HUH?
- KAEDE.
- I HAVE RECONSIDERED.
- I, TOO, AM A PRIESTESS.
I SHALL RECOVER
MY SISTER'S ASHES
ON MY OWN STRENGTH.
INUYASHA, DO ME THE KINDNESS
OF TELLING ME
WHICH DIRECTION URASUE
WAS LAST TRAVELING.
- ARE YOU TRYING
TO GET YOURSELF KILLED?
- DON'T BE SO HARSH.
I'M GOING.
I SHALL DEAL WITH
THE CONSEQUENCES
WHEN I ARRIVE.
- YOU'RE IN NO CONDITION
TO GO, KAEDE.
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR BREATH
TRYING TO STOP HER.
SHE'S A STUBBORN AS AN OX.
YOU'LL NEVER TALK HER OUT OF IT.
HMPH.
COME ON.
MOVE IT ALONG, GRANNY.
WE'LL LAY KIKYO'S REMAINS
TO REST AGAIN.
- INUYASHA, THANK YOU.
- SOMETHING TELLS ME
SHIPPO AND I
HAD BETTER COME WITH YOU.
- KAGOME.
- IT WASN'T ME HE WAS
LOOKING AT JUST NOW.
HE WAS LOOKING RIGHT THROUGH ME,
TO KIKYO.
KAEDE'S FALLEN ASLEEP.
- HMPH.
LET'S GET SOME SLEEP OURSELVES.
WE'VE GOT A BIG BATTLE TOMORROW.
- WHAT?
ALREADY?
- I CAN SMELL THE REMAINS.
THEY'RE NOT FAR OFF.
- INUYASHA?
HE FELL ASLEEP.
HE WAS SLEEPING THE FIRST TIME
I SAW HIM, TOO.
ACTUALLY, HE WAS UNDER A SPELL,
BUT TO ME, IT LOOKED LIKE
HE WAS MERELY ASLEEP.
I THOUGHT HE HATED KIKYO.
I GET IT!
THIS ALL ABOUT ME
LOOKING LIKE KIKYO.
THAT'S IT, ISN'T IT?
THAT'S WHY YOU CAN'T LOOK AT ME!
[GASP]
INUYASHA!
- IT'S NOT...
[SIGH]
- HUH?
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
[GASP]
WHEN HE HELD MY HAND
AND LOOKED AT ME,
IT WASN'T A LOOK OF HATRED
IN HIS EYES.
MY HEART'S STILL POUNDING.
COULD IT BE THAT...
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT HE'S BEEN
HIDING HIS FEELINGS ALL ALONG?
THAT HE ACTUALLY LOVED KIKYO?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[YAWN]
- I MUST RETRIEVE
KIKYO'S REMAINS QUICKLY,
LEST URASUE USE THEM
TO SOME EVIL END.
I FEAR TROUBLE LIES
IN THE PATH AHEAD,
DREADFUL TROUBLE.
- OH, GOOD.
THAT'S JUST WHAT
WE NEED TO HEAR.
IF YOU WERE SO WORRIED
ABOUT HER REMAINS,
WHY DIDN'T YOU
SCATTER THEM IN THE RIVER
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
WE WOULDN'T BE
IN THIS PREDICAMENT
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU
AND YOUR SENTIMENTALITY.
- INUYASHA, HAVE YE NO REGARD
FOR MAN'S
GRAVESITES AND TOMBSTONES?
A GRAVE IS MORE THAN SIMPLY
A PLACE TO BURY A BODY OR ASHES.
IT IS A PLACE OF REFUGE,
OF SHELTER FOR THE HEARTS
OF THOSE LOVED ONES LEFT BEHIND.
- THE LOVED ONES LEFT BEHIND?
- MY SISTER WAS BORN
A PRIESTESS.
SHE USED HER POWERS
FOR THE GOOD OF THE VILLAGERS.
SHE WARDED SPECTERS AND DEMONS
AWAY FROM THE VILLAGE
AND BATTLED ILLNESS AND FAMINE
COUNTLESS TIMES.
EVER SINCE HER DEMISE,
KIKYO'S SPIRIT
CONTINUES TO ENCOURAGE THEM
TO OVERCOME THEIR OBSTACLES
AND HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO CARRY ON.
BUT PEOPLE ARE WEAK,
AND HEARTS ARE EASILY SWAYED
BY THE WINDS OF DANGER
AND UNCERTAINTY.
HER GRAVE WAS A PLACE
OF REASSURANCE, A HAVEN,
TO ENCOURAGE THE VILLAGERS
TO BRACE THEMSELVES
AGAINST THE STORMS OF LIFE.
- INUYASHA LOOKS JUST LIKE
HE DID BEFORE.
HE'S THINKING OF KIKYO.
HE WAS IN LOVE WITH HER,
AND YET SHE SHOT HIM
WITH AN ARROW
AND PINNED HIM TO A TREE,
WHERE HE SLEPT IN A SPELL
FOR 50 YEARS.
THE POOR GUY.
- HUH?
- SHE DIDN'T
RETURN HIS FEELINGS.
- HMM.
- SHE DIDN'T LOVE HIM IN RETURN.
SHE DIDN'T LOVE HIM.
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU GAWKING AT?
THAT'S PRETTY BAD, WHEN YOU CAN
EVEN GIVE A HALF-DEMON
THE CREEPS.
- HEH HEH HEH.
- WHAT'S WITH THE SYMPATHETIC
LOOKS YOU'RE GIVING ME?
- OH, NOTHING.
I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT SOMETHING STUPID.
- HMM.
STUPID LIKE WHAT?
- FORGET IT.
[LAUGHS]
- OUT WITH IT!
KAGOME, I WANT SOME ANSWERS NOW!
- WHAT?
DROP IT!
- [LAUGHTER
HEH HEH HEH HEH.
YAAA!
- NOW, THEN.
LET'S SEE WHAT MAGIC
MY DEMON KILN
HAS BROUGHT TO THE MIXTURE
OF ASHES AND GRAVESIDE SOIL.
YES, THIS COULD BE
MY FINEST CREATION YET.
NOW...
[CHUCKLES]
ARISE!
ARISE, KIKYO.
COME TO ME.
KIKYO, THE GREAT PRIESTESS.
YOU FOILED MANY AN ATTEMPT
BY DEMONS AND MONSTERS
TO TAKE POSSESSION
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
OF THE FOUR SOULS.
[CHUCKLES]
THEY SAY THAT
IF A DEMON SHOULD POSSESS
BUT A SINGLE SHARD
OF THE BROKEN JEWEL,
ITS POWERS AS A DEMON
WILL AT LEAST DOUBLE
IN STRENGTH.
I NEED THEM.
I MUST HAVE EVERY FRAGMENT
OF THE JEWEL FOR MYSELF.
GO FORTH AND DESTROY EVERY DEMON
IN SEARCH OF
THE JEWEL FRAGMENTS.
BURN THEM ALIVE.
I HAVE BROUGHT YOU BACK,
AND YOU SHALL SERVE
MY EVERY WISH.
NOW GO, AND RETRIEVE
THE JEWEL SHARDS!
HA HA HA HA.
HA HA HA HA HA!
IMPOSSIBLE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HMM.
THE BODY HAS REVIVED,
BUT THE SOUL DID NOT RETURN.
WHY, UNPARALLELED MAGIC
COULD NOT FAIL
TO BRING BACK THE SOUL.
WAIT.
THIS COULD ONLY HAVE HAPPENED
IF THE SOUL
WERE ALREADY REINCARNATED
INTO ANOTHER BODY.
[GRR]
I HAVE NO USE
FOR THIS BODY OF KIKYO'S
UNLESS IT HAS A SOUL!
[GASP]
ALL THIS TIME AND MAGIC WASTED.
WASTED ON REVIVING
THAT USELESS SHELL OF A HUMAN.
NOW HOW WILL I
RETRIEVE THE JEWELS?
HOW?
- WHAT ARE THOSE?
- MUMMIES?
CLAY STATUES, MAYBE?
OH, THEY'RE GIVING ME
THE WILLIES.
- SOMETHING TELLS ME
THAT'S THE PLACE.
- OH, GREAT.
WE GOT TO CROSS
THIS RICKETY OLD BRIDGE?
- FREAK ME OUT!
- STAY HERE IF YOU'RE
THAT SCARED OF CROSSING.
I'LL GO ON MY OWN
AND GET THE REMAINS BACK, OK?
- YEAH, AS IF.
I'LL JUST STAND HERE
A COUPLE HUNDRED FEET
ABOVE GROUND,
BLOWING IN THE WIND!
- COME, THEN, IF YOU WANT.
- WAIT! AREN'T YOU GOING
TO HELP ME ACROSS?
- UHH!
HEY, HOW'D THOSE GET HERE?
WE GOT TROUBLE!
- MUST BE URASUE'S SOLDIERS.
- THE CLAY MUMMIES
WE SAW IN THE FOREST.
UH-OH.
THAT MEANS...
INUYASHA!
THEY'RE CLOSING IN FROM BEHIND!
- HANG ON TIGHT, LADIES.
THIS SWINGING BRIDGE IS
ABOUT TO LIVE UP TO ITS NAME.
IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
HMM?
THESE THINGS REALLY ARE
MADE OF MUD.
- FOXFIRE!
- OOH!
- UHH! UHH!
- UHH! YAA!
I WISH ALL MY ENEMIES
WERE THIS WEAK.
- UHH!
TOO BAD THERE'S
SO MANY OF 'EM!
- WHAT CAN ALL THAT RUCKUS
BE OUTSIDE?
I'LL GO SEE FOR MYSELF,
AND WORK OFF SOME FRUSTRATION.
[GRUNTING]
RELEASE IT.
THIS HERB BELONGS TO ME!
- INUYASHA, LOOK OUT!
SHE'S MOVED ON HER OWN.
WAIT!
THAT MUST BE
KIKYO'S REINCARNATION.
SHE'S ALMOST HER DOUBLE.
HOW FORTUITOUS FOR ME.
THE RESEMBLANCE IS REMARKABLE.
THAT MUST BE HER.
- UHH!
HUH--UHH!
UHH!
HUH?
- YAAA!
YAA!
- AAAH!
[SCREAMING]
- AAH!
- WHOA!
- AAAH!
- OH, NO!
KAEDE! SHIPPO!
UHH.
RELEASE ME!
LET ME GO!
AAH!
- PREFER TO FALL TO YOUR DEATH,
YOUNG MAIDEN?
AFTER ALL MY HARD WORK
TRYING TO REVIVE THAT CORPSE,
I WON'T EASILY GIVE UP
ITS REINCARNATED SOUL.
I HAVE PLANS IN STORE FOR YOU,
PLANS TO BRING BACK KIKYO.
- BRING BACK KIKYO?
I DON'T LIKE THE SOUNDS OF THAT.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- THE PRIESTESS KIKYO,
WHO DIED 50 YEARS AGO,
IS BROUGHT BACK,
SEEING AS THE SECRET
SHIKON JEWEL
BURST FROM MY BODY,
THEN PERHAPS I REALLY AM
HER REINCARNATION.
URASUE FORCES ME
TO DRINK A POTION,
SUCKING THE SOUL
FROM MY VERY BODY.
KIKYO AND INUYASHA ARE REUNITED
AFTER A 50-YEAR SEPARATION,
BUT IT'S FAR FROM HAPPY.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.