- [SIGH]
- WHOO-HOO!
THERE'S EVERY WEAPON
UNDER THE SUN HERE--
ALL MADE FROM THE BONES
AND HIDE OF DEMONS.
- THE PEOPLE OF THIS VILLAGE
USE THESE ARMS
TO SLAY DEMONS.
- THEY MUST HAVE BEEN
PRETTY STRONG FOR HUMANS.
- YES. THAT'S WHY THE DEMONS HAD
SUCH ANGER TOWARDS THIS PLACE.
- OH. NARAKU TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF THEIR HATRED.
- HE USED THE DEMONS
TO DO HIS DIRTY WORK.
- ON OUR JOURNEY IN SEARCH
OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
WE CAME UPON A VILLAGE
OF DEMON SLAYERS.
LEGEND SAYS THIS VILLAGE
WAS THE BIRTHPLACE
OF THE SACRED JEWEL,
BUT NARAKU'S TREACHERY
BEAT US TO THE SPOT,
AND THE ENTIRE VILLAGE
WAS ANNIHILATED BEFORE
WE GOT THERE.
EVERY SLAYER, EXCEPT FOR
A GIRL CALLED SANGO, WAS KILLED.
THE SACRED JEWEL THAT KIKYO HAS
TRIED TO HIDE FROM THE WORLD,
THE SACRED JEWEL THAT BURST
FROM MY BODY EONS LATER,
EVERYTHING WOULD BECOME CLEAR
IN THIS VILLAGE.
- [BIRDS SCREECHING]
- DAMN IT,
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE, ANYWAY?
HEY, MIROKU,
IS THAT SANGO GIRL
STILL IN BED HEALING
HER WOUNDS OR WHAT?
- YES, I BELIEVE SHE IS.
- WELL, SHE CAN'T SLEEP
ALL DAY.
GET HER OUT OF BED.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE WHO KNOWS
WHERE NARAKU'S HIDING.
SHE SAYS SHE CAN'T
REMEMBER HOW TO GET
TO THE CASTLE
WHERE HE'S STAYING,
BUT IF WE KEEP
LOOKING AROUND,
SOMETHING'S BOUND TO JOG
HER MEMORY SOONER OR LATER.
- MUST HAVE BEEN A SPELL.
AND NOW THAT IT'S WORN OFF,
SHE'S FORGOTTEN EVERYTHING ABOUT
NARAKU AND HIS WHEREABOUTS.
- WHO CARES ABOUT
HER SPELL AND WOUNDS?
WE'VE BEEN WAITING 10 DAYS!
I WOULD HAVE BEEN UP IN 3.
- NOT ME. I WOULD BE BEDRIDDEN
FOR AT LEAST A MONTH.
BESIDES, SANGO'S NOT JUST
SUFFERING PHYSICALLY.
SHE'S LOST HER
ENTIRE FAMILY AND VILLAGE.
HER HEART'S
BEEN DEEPLY WOUNDED.
- OH, A WOUNDED HEART, HUH?
WELL, THE BEST CURE
FOR THAT IS VENGEANCE.
AND TO GET OUR REVENGE,
WE HAVE TO FIND NARAKU'S CASTLE.
I'M GONNA SEE
IF SHE REMEMBERS ANYTHING.
UGH! WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
- LEAVE HER ALONE
AND LET HER REST FOR AWHILE.
I GUARANTEE THAT WILL BE
THE BEST MEDICINE.
- [GASP]
SHE'S GONE!
SANGO,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD BE UP.
YOU STILL NEED TO REST.
- THE GRAVES.
- HUH?
- YOU BURIED ALL THE VILLAGERS,
AND YOU MARKED THEIR GRAVES.
- MMM...UH...
I CAN'T TELL HER TO CHEER UP.
I MEAN, IN ONE DAY,
SHE'S SUDDENLY ALL
ALONE IN THE WORLD.
- LISTEN,
WHEN YOUR WOUNDS HEAL,
WHY DON'T YOU CONSIDER
JOINING OUR GROUP?
INUYASHA AND MIROKU
ARE PRETTY DECENT GUYS,
GIVE OR TAKE A FEW QUIRKS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- THAT'S A SACRED JEWEL SHARD
AROUND YOUR NECK, ISN'T IT?
- HUH?
THE SHARDS FROM THE SACRED JEWEL
ENERGIZE THE POWER OF EVIL.
I'VE STILL GOT A LOT OF PIECES
TO COLLECT BEFORE IT'S WHOLE.
- NARAKU WILL COME AFTER IT,
I'M POSITIVE.
THAT'S WHY I WANT TO JOIN YOU
AND YOUR FRIENDS.
- TO AVENGE YOUR
FAMILY AND VILLAGE?
- I GUESS SO.
BESIDES, THE SHIKON JEWEL...
- WAS BORN HERE,
SO I'VE BEEN TOLD.
ALL OF US INITIALLY CAME
TO YOUR VILLAGE
HOPING TO LEARN MORE
ABOUT THE JEWEL'S ORIGINS.
EVERYONE WHO COMES IN CONTACT
WITH THE JEWEL SHARD
SEEMS TO END UP UNHAPPY.
JUST WHAT IS IT,
EXACTLY?
- [MEWLING]
- HMM?
HEY, WHAT'S UP, KIRARA?
- ALL RIGHT.
CALL YOUR FRIENDS.
- HUH?
- YOU HELPED BURY THE DEAD.
SO I WILL TELL YOU
HOW THE SACRED JEWEL CAME TO BE.
- AT LONG LAST, WE'LL BE ABLE
TO ENTER THE LIMESTONE CAVE,
THE BIRTHPLACE OF
THE JEWEL OF 4 SOULS.
- SO TELL US, SANGO,
HOW WE GET RID OF THIS STUPID
CAVE BARRIER, ANYWAY?
- WE NEED TO KNOW WHAT AGE-OLD
INCANTATION YOU VILLAGERS CHANT
IN ORDER TO BREAK IT
AND PASS THROUGH SAFELY.
- THERE ISN'T
ANY INCANTATION.
- OH! OF COURSE THERE IS.
HOW ELSE WOULD YOU DO IT?
- MYOGA!
- OY!
- THIS PLACE IS A GRAVEYARD.
- GRAVEYARD?
- IT'S USELESS
TO JUST LOOK FOR A WAY IN.
AT FIRST, MY VILLAGERS
HAD THOUGHT THE DEMONS
HAD PLACED A CURSE TO KEEP
ANYONE FROM ENTERING,
BUT WE EVENTUALLY REALIZED
THAT SHE IS THE ONE
WHO KEEPS INTRUDERS OUT.
- AND WHO IS SHE?
- THE PERSON IN WHOM
THE SACRED JEWEL WAS BORN.
HER SPIRIT IS FULL
OF SADNESS AND REGRET,
AND IT PREVENTS OTHERS
FROM ENTERING.
THAT'S WHAT I SENSE.
IT WILL BE EASIER TO UNDERSTAND
ONCE WE GO IN.
GO AHEAD, STEP THROUGH
THE BARRIER.
- UHH...
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- COUNTLESS PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN KILLED
BECAUSE OF THE SACRED JEWEL'S
DARK POWER.
AND IT IS THE SYMPATHY
YOU SHOW FOR THE VICTIMS
THAT LEADS ME TO BELIEVE
SHE WILL ALLOW YOU
TO ENTER THE CAVE.
- HUH?
- HEY, SHE'S RIGHT.
WE GOT THROUGH.
- WE DID IT.
NOW WE CAN MEET THE PERSON WHO
GAVE BIRTH TO THE SACRED JEWEL.
HA! ENTER MYOGA!
[SPUTTERING]
NOW, WHY DID THAT HAPPEN?
- UH...AAH!
- UH.
- HUH?
- WHA-WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?
- THERE WAS A TIME WHEN OGRES,
DRAGONS, AND OTHER DEMONS
MERGED THEIR BODIES TOGETHER
TO WAGE A BATTLE.
THEY FOUGHT AGAINST
ONE POWERFUL HUMAN.
- THERE'S A PERSON
INSIDE THE STALAGMITE.
- THE DEMON HAS IT
IN HER JAWS.
- ANCIENT ARMOR.
IS THAT AN ANCIENT WARRIOR?
- IT'S A WOMAN,
A PRIESTESS WHO LIVED
MANY CENTURIES AGO.
- HUH?
- LOOK AT THE NUMBER
OF DEMONS SURROUNDING HER.
THIS PRIESTESS MUST HAVE HAD
IMMENSE SPIRITUAL POWER.
- THE COURT NOBLES CONTROLLED
THE COUNTRY AT THAT TIME.
WARS AND FAMINES
DRAGGED ON AND ON,
AND COUNTLESS PEOPLE PERISHED.
DEMONS DEVOURED THE DEAD
AND THE NEAR DEAD,
AND THEY WERE ABLE TO GROW
IN GREAT NUMBERS.
MANY PRIESTS AND WARRIORS
SET OUT TO SLAY THEM,
BUT ONLY ONE PRIESTESS,
KNOWN AS MIDORIKO,
WAS ABLE TO PURIFY DEMON SOULS
AND RENDER THEM HARMLESS.
SHE WAS CONSIDERED THE MOST
POWERFUL HUMAN OF HER TIME.
- SHE COULD PURIFY AND WEAKEN
THE DEMONS' SOULS?
- MM-HMM.
IN HER WORLD, HUMANS, ANIMALS,
TREES, AND EVEN STONES
WERE ALL CREATED
THROUGH THE 4 SOULS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
SHIKON MEANS "4 SOULS."
- I'VE COME ACROSS THAT
PHILOSOPHY IN MY READINGS.
THE 4 SOULS ARE CALLED
ARA-MITAMA, NIGI-MITAMA,
KUSHI-MITAMA, AND SAKI-MITAMA.
WHEN THEY'RE COMBINED,
THEY BECOME THE SOUL
OF ONE PERSON
HOUSED INSIDE THE HEART.
ARA-MITAMA IS COURAGE.
NIGI-MITAMA IS FRIENDSHIP.
KUSHI-MITAMA IS WISDOM.
SAKI-MITAMA IS LOVE.
WHEN THE 4 SOULS, OR SPIRITS,
WORK TOGETHER IN HARMONY,
IT IS CALLED NAOHI,
AND THE HUMAN HEART
IS FILLED WITH GOODNESS.
ARE YOU KEEPING UP WITH ME,
INUYASHA?
- UH, NO, NOT REALLY.
- THIS IS WAY
TOO DEEP FOR ME.
- WHEN SOMEBODY
DOES A BAD DEED,
THE 4 SOULS ENERGIZE EVIL,
AND THE HUMAN LOSES HIS WAY.
IN OTHER WORDS--
- IN OTHER WORDS,
A SOUL CAN TURN GOOD OR BAD,
AND THIS TRANSFORMATION
CAN HAPPEN WITHIN A HUMAN
SOUL OR A DEMON SOUL.
NOW YOU KNOW WHY MIDORIKO
WAS A FORMIDABLE FOE
FOR THE DEMONS,
BECAUSE SHE WAS ABLE
TO PURIFY THEIR SOULS
AND MAKE THEM POWERLESS.
- SO WHAT? SHE FOUGHT OFF
AN ARMY OF DEMONS
BY TURNING THEM INTO
A BUNCH OF WEAKLINGS.
HER POWER DIDN'T LAST
VERY LONG, DID IT?
I'D SAY SHE'S A PRETTY
USELESS PRIESTESS NOW.
- SHE HASN'T LOST
THE BATTLE YET.
- WHAT DOES SHE MEAN,
NOT YET?
[GASP]
WHAT'S THAT?
- AFTER BATTLING FOR
7 DAYS AND 7 NIGHTS,
A DEMON GOT ITS FANGS
INTO MIDORIKO.
WITH HER LAST OUNCE
OF ENERGY,
SHE REACHED DEEP WITHIN
HER OWN BODY FOR STRENGTH,
AND SEIZED THE DEMON'S SOUL.
BUT IN DOING SO,
SHE FORCED OUT HER OWN SOUL.
- TELL ME, IS THE HOLE
IN HER CHEST
THE SPOT WHERE SHE FORCED OUT
HER OWN SOUL?
- WHAT FLEW OUT OF HER WAS
IN FACT THE SHIKON JEWEL.
SHE WASN'T ABLE TO PURIFY
THE DEMON'S SOUL.
ALL SHE COULD DO WAS
SEIZE AND IMPRISON IT
ALONG WITH HERSELF.
ALTHOUGH THE FLESH IS GONE,
INSIDE THE SACRED JEWEL,
A BATTLE STILL WAGES
BETWEEN MIDORIKO
AND THE DEMONS.
THAT IS WHY THE FIGHT
ISN'T OVER YET.
- SO, A WAR BETWEEN SOULS
IS STILL RAGING INSIDE
THE SACRED JEWEL.
- HA. IT'S NOT LIKE THIS STORY
COMPLICATES THINGS.
WE JUST HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT NARAKU HUNTING
AFTER THE JEWEL SHARDS.
I'M GONNA TAKE POSSESSION
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
AND USE IT TO BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON,
AND THEN MIDORIKO
CAN REST IN PEACE.
HUH? HUH? AAH!
[SCREAMING]
AAH!
- LOOKS LIKE PEOPLE WHO
TALK OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
AND SELFISH GAIN
GET THROWN FROM THE CAVE.
- THAT MUST BE MIDORIKO'S
VERSION OF "SIT."
- IT'S GOTTEN SO LATE.
- A PRIESTESS INSIDE
OF A STALAGMITE?
OH, MY! TELL ME ALL
THE JUICY DETAILS, SHIPPO.
- THE PRIESTESS THRUST
THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL
OUT OF HER BODY
WHILE THE DEMON HAD HER
IN HIS JAWS,
AND THE IMAGE OF THEM
IS SET IN STONE.
- HMM. THEY WERE COVERED
IN A STALAGMITE.
THEN SEVERAL CENTURIES MUST HAVE
PASSED SINCE THE BATTLE,
JUST LIKE SANGO SAID.
- MY VILLAGERS HAVE WORKED
AS SLAYERS FOR GENERATION
UPON GENERATION,
AND IT LIKELY HAS SOMETHING
TO DO WITH MIDORIKO'S INFLUENCE.
OVER THE CENTURIES,
THE SACRED JEWEL PASSED
THROUGH THE HANDS OF
SEVERAL HUMANS AND DEMONS,
AND EVENTUALLY RETURNED HERE
IN MY GRANDFATHER'S TIME.
THE SHIKON JEWEL CAME OUT
OF A DEMON THAT HE HAD SLAIN.
BUT MY GRANDFATHER'S LIFE
AND THE LIVES OF MANY OTHERS
WERE SACRIFICED IN THE BATTLE.
THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL
WAS REMOVED FROM THE DEMON,
BUT IT WAS HORRIBLY DEFILED,
AND THE SLAYERS DID NOT POSSESS
THE ABILITY TO HANDLE IT.
- SO THEY PUT IT
IN KIKYO'S CARE.
- KIKYO? WAS SHE THE PRIESTESS
WHO HAD THE ABILITY
TO PURIFY THE SACRED JEWEL?
- YES, BUT NARAKU FOUND OUT
ABOUT HER AND KILLED HER.
- WHEN DEMONS AND EVIL HUMANS
POSSESS IT,
THE JEWEL BECOMES DEFILED.
WHEN A PURE-HEARTED SOUL
POSSESSES IT,
THE JEWEL TRANSFORMS
AND BECOMES PURE.
- IT'S ALL VERY COMPLICATED.
IT'S A SACRED JEWEL
THAT POSSESSES THE POWER
FOR GOOD OR EVIL,
BUT I'VE NEVER HEARD OF
AN INSTANCE WHERE THE JEWEL
HAS BEEN USED FOR GOOD.
AND AS LONG AS NARAKU
IS AFTER IT,
THERE WILL ONLY BE
MORE AND MORE BLOODSHED.
SO WE MUST PUT AN END TO
THE SACRED JEWEL'S BAD KARMA.
INUYASHA, YOU MUST
RELINQUISH ALL THOUGHTS
OF USING THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL
TO BECOME A GREAT DEMON.
- HA!
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
I HAVE TO FOCUS ON
DESTROYING NARAKU.
- [SNIFFING]
[SNIFFING]
- VERY GOOD.
THANK YOU, KIRARA.
WE MADE GOOD TIME
COMING HERE.
MIDORIKO, I, TOO, FEEL
COMPASSION FOR HUMANS.
HOWEVER, WHEN ONE LIVES
AS LONG AS I HAVE AND SEES
A GREAT DEAL OF DEATH,
ONE BECOMES ACCUSTOMED
TO IT, HARDENED.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
THIS AFTERNOON I WAS TOO EAGER
IN MY PURSUIT FOR THE TRUTH,
BUT SINCE YOU'VE ALLOWED ME
TO PASS THE BARRIER,
I TAKE IT YOU UNDERSTAND.
- [MEWLING]
- OH, SORRY.
SORRY, KIRARA.
I'LL BE FINISHED HERE SOON.
[GRUNTING]
DAMN ARTHRITIS.
SO MANY HUGE DEMONS.
A SINGLE PRIESTESS TOOK ON
THIS MANY DEMONS AT ONCE?
UNBELIEVABLE.
SIMPLY UNBELIEVABLE.
NUMEROUS SMALLER DEMONS MERGED
TOGETHER TO FORM HUGE ONES.
WHAT'S THAT IN HER ARMOR?
OOH. I BET THAT'S
THE HOLE IN HER CHEST
WHERE THE SACRED JEWEL
WAS FORCED OUT.
YEP. IT MUST BE,
JUDGING FROM THE SIZE.
[RUMBLING]
- OH! WHAT'S GOING ON? AAH!
- [GROWL]
- I HAVE A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
DAMN! IT'S THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
THE DEMONS WHO WEREN'T
COMPLETELY SUBDUED
ARE TRYING TO REVIVE!
AAH! AAH!
[GROANING]
- [ROAR]
[GROWLING]
DAMN! IT'S THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
THE DEMONS WHO WEREN'T
COMPLETELY SUBDUED
ARE TRYING TO REVIVE!
- [ROAR]
- UNH! WHAT WAS
THAT TREMOR?
- INUYASHA! THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD IS GONE!
- SOMETHING'S HAPPENING
IN MIDORIKO'S CAVE.
- UNH! UNH!
MYOGA IS MISSING, KAGOME.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE HE WENT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE HE TOOK OFF
WITH INUYASHA.
- NOT A CHANCE.
THAT LITTLE COWARD NEVER STICKS
HIS NOSE INTO DANGER.
HE ALWAYS HIDES
WHEN THERE'S TROUBLE.
MYOGA, WHERE ARE YOU?
- WHERE'S KIRARA?
- KIRARA, RUN!
CALL INUYASHA AND MIROKU!
- [ROARING]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
KIRARA?
OH, RIGHT. WE HAVE TO GET
THE JEWEL SHARD BACK.
- [WHIMPERING]
- KIRARA! OH!
- [ROARING]
- DEMON SPIRITS.
THEY'RE TRANSFORMING
INTO SOMETHING FOUL.
- [ROAR]
- HANG ON, KIRARA,
PLEASE.
THIS ISN'T LOOKING TOO GOOD.
- [ROAR]
- THAT'S--
[GASP]
WHAT?
THE PRIESTESS MIDORIKO!
- [GRUNT]
HURRY, MIROKU!
- UNH! FOUND IT.
I SHOULDN'T LINGER HERE
WITH THE JEWEL SHARD.
I HAVE TO LEAVE THE CAVE.
- GO!
NOW THAT'S OVER WITH.
I ONLY KNOW ONE CREATURE
ON THE FACE OF THIS WHOLE EARTH
WHO WOULD PULL A STUNT
AS STUPID AS THIS ONE.
- OH! IT'S YOU,
MASTER INUYASHA.
THANK GOODNESS NOTHING
TOO SERIOUS HAS HAPPENED.
- OH, CUT THE CRAP,
WILL YOU?
WHY'D YOU DRAG THE JEWEL SHARD
OUT TO A PLACE LIKE THIS
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT?
- I WAS ASLEEP ON KIRARA'S BACK,
AND BEFORE I KNEW IT,
SHE HAD TAKEN ME HERE.
- [GROWL]
- YOU LIAR!
- IT'S TRUE!
AND WHEN WE GOT HERE,
THE DEMON SPIRITS THAT STILL
HAD SOME EVIL ENERGY IN THEM
REACTED AND REVIVED WITH
THE LIGHT FROM THE SACRED JEWEL.
- I COULD HAVE TOLD YOU
THAT WOULD HAPPEN, YOU IDIOT.
TRYING TO SMOOTH OVER THE FACT
THAT YOU WERE NEARLY KILLED.
HUH. I SHOULD NEVER
HAVE BOTHERED SAVING YOU.
- EXCUSE ME,
MASTER INUYASHA,
BUT I DON'T RECALL YOU
EVER ACTUALLY SAVING ME.
- USE YOUR LITTLE BRAIN.
DON'T BE SO DUMB.
- I'M NOT BEING DUMB.
THE PRIESTESS MIDORIKO
SAVED ME, NOT YOU.
- SAVE YOUR DREAMING
FOR SLEEP.
- [GROANING]
- [PURRING]
- OLD MYOGA'S BEEN DOING
SOME INVESTIGATION
INTO THE STORY
OF THE SACRED JEWEL,
AND HE FEELS THAT IT WAS
IMPOSSIBLE FOR ONE PRIESTESS
TO BATTLE SO MANY DEMONS,
NO MATTER HOW STRONG
HER SPIRITUAL POWER.
MAYBE MIDORIKO HAD
A BRILLIANT HELPER BY HER SIDE.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- THE DEMON SLAYER SANGO
HAS DECIDED TO JOIN US
IN OUR JOURNEY.
IT MIGHT BE MY IMAGINATION,
BUT MIROKU SEEMS
REALLY HAPPY ABOUT THAT.
WE COME TO A VILLAGE SUFFERING
FROM FREQUENT FLOODING,
AND FIND OUT THAT THERE'S
A WATER GOD DEMANDING
CHILD SACRIFICES IN RETURN
FOR PROTECTING THEM.
WHAT KIND OF GOD DOES THAT?
THIS MIGHT BE A DEMON
WITH A SHARD OF THE SACRED JEWEL
THAT'S DOING THIS.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!