- TORN BETWEEN THE DEMON
AND HUMAN WORLDS,
HALF-DEMON INUYASHA
HOPES TO BECOME ALL DEMON
WITH THE JEWEL OF 4 SOULS.
DESPISING SUCH
A YOUNGER BROTHER,
COLD-HEARTED SESSHOMARU
CONCOCTS A PLAN.
SEEING HIS LONG-DEAD MOTHER
IN A SKYBORNE CARRIAGE,
INUYASHA REACTS
WITH RAGE AND SORROW.
SURELY, HIS HUMAN MOTHER
CANNOT DESERVE SUCH SUFFERING.
- OH!
- NICE TRY, JERK!
SHE'S BEEN DEAD FOR YEARS,
AND WE BOTH KNOW IT!
LIKE I'D REALLY FALL FOR
SOME STUPID TRICK LIKE THAT!
- A TRICK, IS IT?
- YOU'RE WHO'S STUPID.
RECALLING SPIRITS
FROM THE NETHERWORLD
IS A SIMPLE TASK,
IF YOU ARE LORD SESSHOMARU.
HE WAS EVEN SO KIND
AS TO GIVE HER FLESH,
AND YET HER OWN SON
WOULD DENY IT.
HOW SAD TO BE MOTHER
TO ONE SUCH AS YOU!
- I HAVE COME BACK,
INUYASHA!
BACK FROM THE WORLD
OF THE DEAD!
[GROANING]
- IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
[MOANS]
- YOU'RE WORTHLESS!
- MOTHER!
- INUYASHA!
- AAH!
[GASPS]
- LADY KAGOME!
LADY KAGOME! LADY KAGOME!
- OH! OH, NO!
OVER HERE!
[CHATTER]
- MOM, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT HERE?
- OH, DID I WAKE YOU UP?
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST LOWERING THE BIKE SEAT
HERE FOR YOUR SISTER.
REMEMBER?
SHE LEFT HER BIKE OVER THERE,
BUT HERE SHE CAN USE MINE.
FIRST, THOUGH, I THOUGHT
I SHOULD LOWER THE SEAT
SO THAT SHE WON'T FALL DOWN.
- SHE'LL BE GONE A COUPLE
OF DAYS THIS TIME.
HER BACKPACK HAD
A LOT OF CLOTHES.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
BUT IF SHE HAS
A BIKE READY AT HOME,
SHE'LL HAVE LESS TO WORRY
ABOUT WHEN SHE GETS BACK.
- SHE'S LUCKY TO HAVE YOU
TO WORRY ABOUT HER.
I'M SURE GLAD I DON'T
MAKE YOU WORRY LIKE THAT.
- BUT I DO.
HOW CAN I HELP IT?
I'M YOUR MOM.
YOU DO STILL WET THE BED--
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, MOM!
I DON'T DO THAT!
I'M IN THIRD GRADE.
REMEMBER?
[CHUCKLES]
- ALL I REALLY WANT
IS FOR YOU TWO TO BE HAPPY.
- THANKS. I KNOW.
QUICK! MAKE A WISH!
TO BE HAPPY...
OH, AND WIN THE LOTTERY.
[GASPING]
- HER FACE! NO REFLECTION!
INUYASHA. INU--
MY VOICE! I CAN'T SPEAK!
INUYASHA! SNAP OUT OF IT!
SHE DOESN'T HAVE A FACE!
WHOEVER SHE IS,
SHE'S NOT YOUR MOM!
- INUYASHA, I MUST RETURN NOW
TO THE NETHERWORLD.
- D-DO YOU HAVE TO?
- THE PETALS...
LOOK INTO THE WATER.
- HUH?
THAT'S ME, BACK WHEN
I WAS STILL SMALL.
- YOU REMEMBER.
THAT'S GOOD.
AS A CHILD, I OFTEN
HELD YOU THAT WAY.
I HELD YOU TO MY HEART,
JUST AS I AM DOING NOW.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
I'LL NEVER LET GO.
NOT NOW. NOT EVER.
[GROANING]
- MOTHER.
- INUYASHA!
I'M STILL STUCK.
WHY CAN'T I MOVE?
HUH?
[CHATTERING AND SQUEAKING]
IT'S AN ILLUSION!
THIS PLACE, HIS MOM,
ALL OF IT!
- KAGOME! SNAP OUT OF IT!
IT'S ME! ME!
MYOGA THE FLEA!
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT SESSHOMARU,
INUYASHA'S OLDER BROTHER,
WOULD BE THE ONE
SEEKING THE TOMB?
AND WHAT A FOE HE IS!
AND HERE'S KAGOME, POOR THING,
CHAINED HEAD TO TOE,
SO WRAPPED UP,
SHE COULDN'T EVEN SWAT A...
COULDN'T EVEN SWAT A...
[MUMBLING]
[SQUEAKING]
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
I'M LESS PARALYZED
THAN I THOUGHT.
- HAPPY TO HEAR IT.
OH!
[GRUNTING]
HUH?
- MY BOY! MY PRECIOUS BOY!
[GRUMBLING]
- STOP!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[GRUNTS]
NO SOUL-SUCKING
TILL I TELL YOU!
- SORRY.
- YOU CAN HAVE YOUR WAY
WITH HIM LATER,
AFTER HE TELLS US
HOW TO FIND THE TOMB
OF LORD SESSHOMARU
AND INUYASHA'S FATHER.
- SO THAT'S JAKEN,
SESSHOMARU'S EVIL HENCHMAN.
- RIGHT, BUT KEEP
YOUR EYE ON HIS STAFF.
- HMM.
- INUYASHA.
INUYASHA!
YOUR FATHER'S TOMB--
WHERE IS IT?
PLEASE TELL ME.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- THEN THINK HARDER.
LET ME SEE INTO YOUR HEART.
WHAT'S THAT?
- BLACK PEARL, ON THE RIGHT.
- WHAT BLACK PEARL?
WHERE?
WE NEED MORE THAN THAT!
GO DEEPER!
- BUT, LORD JAKEN,
IF I DELVE DEEPER,
HIS SPIRIT WILL BE BROKEN.
- I DON'T CARE!
DO IT!
[SIGHS]
- INUYASHA.
SHH...
- MOTHER, I CAN'T BREATHE.
HUH?
[GASPS]
HER FACE!
THAT MEANS SHE--
[GRUNTING]
[CHOKING]
- WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG?
GET A MOVE ON BEFORE
LORD SESSHOMARU COMES BACK AND--
HUH? OOH!
- YOU MEAN, STUPID,
LITTLE TOAD!
- AAH!
[SIGHS]
WAIT!
LET HIM GO! PLEASE!
- NO!
- INUYASHA!
[PANTING]
AAH! AAH!
SHE'S SUCKING HIM INTO HER!
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
- KAGOME! HIS SPIRIT!
AWAKEN IT!
- SPIRIT? BUT HOW AM I--
- BEHOLD, THE UNMOTHER,
BORN FROM THE GRIEF OF LOSING
CHILDREN TO FAMINE AND WAR.
SHE SEEKS TO FILL
THE VOID WITHIN HERSELF
BY TAKING THE SPIRITS OF OTHERS,
IN THIS CASE, INUYASHA.
- I'M WITH YOU SO FAR,
BUT...HOW DO YOU SUGGEST WE--
[GASPS]
- THAT'S THE WAY.
SOON WE'LL BE TOGETHER ALWAYS.
- THERE'S NO TIME TO--
[GASPS]
THAT CHILD--
IS HE...INUYASHA?
- AN ILLUSION, BUT YES.
THAT'S HOW IT WORKS.
- SO IF I ERASE THE ILLUSION--
[PANTING]
INUYASHA!
SNAP OUT OF IT!
- AAH!
- AAH! UGH!
- OH, INUYASHA!
ARE YOU OK?
[PANTING]
- HOW DARE SHE!
YOU PRETENDED TO BE--
I FELL FOR IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I THOUGHT SHE WAS MY--
- BUT IT WAS JAKEN AND YOUR
BROTHER SESSHOMARU WHO--
- WHAT DID YOU--
AAH!
- INUYASHA.
- HUH?
- I KNOW WHERE IT IS NOW.
[GASPS]
- SESSHOMARU!
[CHOKING]
YOU BAST--
- OF ALL THE PLACES
FOR HIM TO HIDE IT.
ALL THIS TIME,
BENEATH OUR VERY OWN NOSES,
OR, TO BE TECHNICAL,
ABOVE OUR VERY OWN NOSES.
RIGHT ABOVE, ONE MIGHT SAY.
FATHER WAS DETERMINED
TO KEEP IT A SECRET,
WHICH WAS WHY HE CHOSE
HERE TO HIDE IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE MAKING
NO SENSE AT ALL!
- WELL, THEN,
LITTLE BROTHER,
SINCE IT WAS OBVIOUSLY DONE
WITHOUT YOUR KNOWLEDGE,
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME
WITH ME AND FIND OUT?
- AAH! AAH!
- OH!
- LORD INUYASHA!
- AAH!
[GAGGING]
- INUYASHA!
[CHUCKLES]
- NO WONDER SEARCHING FOR IT
BENEATH GROUND WAS USELESS.
SEEING YET NEVER SEEN,
PROTECTED YET NEVER KNOWN
TO ITS PROTECTOR.
OUR FATHER'S TOMB
HIDDEN INSIDE A BLACK PEARL
DEEP WITHIN YOUR EYE.
[GROWLING]
- AND ALL FOR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
YOU PRETENDED
SHE WAS MY MOTHER!
- HMM!
YOU'RE NOT AMUSED?
- NO, I'M NOT!
YOU BASTARD!
- DIE.
- AAH!
AAH! AAH!
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
- HUH?
- THE UNMOTHER!
- SHE GAVE HER LIFE
TO PROTECT HIM.
- DEMON SPIRIT OR NOT,
SHE STILL HAD A MOTHER'S HEART,
AND ISN'T PROTECTING HER CHILD
WHAT A MOTHER CAN'T HELP BUT DO?
- MY BOY!
- HUH?
[GASPS]
[GROWLING]
- HEY, YOU!
- KAGOME, DON'T,
OR HE'LL KILL US BOTH!
- BE QUIET.
- JAKEN.
- HUH?
- AYE, MILORD.
LORD SESSHOMARU, THE STAFF
OF SKULLS IS OURS ONCE MORE.
- AT LAST, THE MOMENT HAS COME.
[CACKLING]
- THE OLD MAN LAUGHS.
IT MEANS THE TOMB WILL OPEN.
- THEY'RE GONE!
- THE PORTAL!
WE MUST MOVE QUICKLY
BEFORE IT'S CLOSED.
DO YOU WANT YOUR BROTHER
TO TAKE SOLE POSSESSION
OF YOUR FATHER'S TREASURE?
- LET HIM.
WHAT DO I CARE?
- BUT, SIRE!
- I NEVER SAID
I'M NOT GOING IN THERE, OK?
SAY YOUR PRAYERS,
SESSHOMARU.
[GROWLING]
YOU'RE DEAD!
YOU STAY HERE!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS
FOR YOU--HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
AN INVITATION?
- HEY!
YOU REALIZE
SESSHOMARU'S THERE.
- WELL, DUH.
THAT'S WHY WE GOT TO GO.
NO ONE DOES THAT,
NO MATTER WHO HE IS.
[SQUAWKING]
AAH!
- FATHER.
- HUH? THOSE BONES THERE
ARE YOUR DAD?
- WHAT ELSE WOULD THEY BE?
[SQUAWKING]
- NOT THAT HE WASN'T
ALIVE ONCE, TOO, BUT...
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WHAT ELSE?
THEY'RE HUGE, OK?
- IT'S TRUE.
THEY'RE HUGE, BECAUSE HIMSELF
WAS OF INCOMPARABLE STATURE.
HERE HE IS, IN TRUEST FORM,
UNDISGUISED,
THE TREASURE SWORD
IMBEDDED IN HIS BONES.
THAT IS WHAT
LORD SESSHOMARU IS AFTER.
- HERE IS WHAT I HAVE SOUGHT.
AT LAST, I SHALL TAKE POSSESSION
OF THE SACRED SWORD.
THE LETHAL, LEGENDARY BLADE
KNOWN TO KILL 100 IN ONE STROKE:
TETSUSAIGA.
- THEY SAY IT WAS
FORGED OF THE FANG
FROM YOUR FATHER'S OWN MOUTH.
ONCE YOU POSSESS
THE BLADE TETSUSAIGA,
YOU POSSESS HIS POWER AS WELL.
AAH! OH!
IT'S NOT STUCK, IS IT?
- FATHER HAS DONE
HIS WORK WELL.
THE BLADE IS ENSORCELLED.
- SESSHOMARU!
- WE'RE NOT FINISHED YET.
AHH!
UGH!
[GROWLS]
NOW WHERE'D HE GO?
HUH?
- BE MORE RESPECTFUL.
IT'S OUR FATHER'S TOMB.
- LOOK WHO'S TALKING!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S HERE
ROBBING HIS GRAVE!
WHY NOT RESPECT HIM
BY LEAVING?
- LORD INUYASHA!
LOOK BACK! LOOK BACK!
- WHERE?
HOW COME?
- DO YOU SEE IT?
THE BLADE FROM
YOUR FATHER'S FANG!
TETSUSAIGA!
- HUH.
WHAT? YOU MEAN THIS?
WHAT A PIECE OF JUNK!
TETSUSAIGA WHAT?
IT WOULDN'T EVEN
CUT PAPER, WET.
- LORD INUYASHA,
YOU MUST DRAW THE SWORD.
PLEASE!
AND YOU, LORD SESSHOMARU,
YOU COULDN'T PULL IT OUT,
COULD YOU?
- DO YOU MEAN TO SAY
INUYASHA CAN?
- OF COURSE.
IT WAS ALWAYS INTENDED THAT
LORD INUYASHA SHOULD INHERIT IT.
HE--HE--HE WAS ENTRUSTED
WITH THE TOMB, WASN'T HE?
THAT SHOULD BE PROOF ENOUGH,
IF YOU ASK ME.
NOW, HURRY!
HURRY AND CLAIM WHAT'S YOURS!
- WHAT ENTRUSTED?
WHAT INHERITANCE?
FOR ALL I CARE, HE CAN KEEP
THE RUSTY PIECE OF JUNK!
[GROWLING]
WHAT I DO MIND, THOUGH,
IS ALL THE OTHER STUFF!
GOOD THING YOU'RE IN A GRAVE,
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO DIE!
[GRUNTING]
- NOW, WHAT THAT AIMED AT ME?
- DAMN!
- YOU FIGHT AS THOUGH
YOU'RE STILL A CHILD.
- YOU CAN'T FIGHT UNARMED.
THE SWORD! GET THE SWORD!
- YOU SHUT UP!
- INUYASHA!
- HUH?
- GET THE DUMB SWORD!
- KAGOME?
- SESSHOMARU COULDN'T
PULL IT OUT, RIGHT?
IF YOU CAN'T HIT HIM
IN THE BODY,
HIT HIM IN THE EGO!
HURT HIS PRIDE!
- HA HA! I GET IT!
I'LL DO IT, IF ONLY TO SEE
THE LOOK ON YOUR FACE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
MORE FUN THAN I THOUGHT.
- N-N-NO!
INUYASHA IS IMMUNE TO THE SPELL
THAT THWARTED SESSHOMARU!
- I KNEW IT!
TETSUSAIGA IS FATED
TO BECOME LORD INUYASHA'S!
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
- PULL HARDER!
DRAW IT OUT!
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
- PULL HARDER!
DRAW IT OUT!
[GRUNTING]
- WHAT?
- HUH?
[LAUGHING]
- YO.
- YES?
- I COULDN'T PULL
THE SWORD OUT, COULD I?
- NOT REALLY. NO.
- ARE YOU DONE?
I AM.
[GRUNTING]
- I DON'T THINK YOU'VE MET
MY POISONED CLAWS.
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
THAT WAS TOO CLOSE.
- RUNNING?
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
- DON'T WORRY, MILORD.
IT'S ALL TAKEN CARE OF--
- AAH!
- YOU COWARD!
- OH! WHY, YOU!
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
- YOU STINKING TOAD!
- YOU STINKING HUMAN!
- THIS HUMAN'S
GOING TO KICK YOUR--
- I DON'T THINK SO!
[GRUNTS]
- KAGOM--UGH!
AAH!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
- NOT EVEN STARTED.
[GASPS]
- AAH!
UGH!
[GROANS]
- THE TIME HAS COME.
DIE.
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
- INUYASHA!
[SNAP]
WHAT?
OOPS.
IT JUST...CAME OUT.
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
SORRY.
NOW WHAT?
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- BORN FROM THE SADNESS
OF LOSING HER CHILDREN
TO HUNGER AND WAR,
THE UNMOTHER ALWAYS GOES AROUND
TRYING TO FILL THAT VOID.
I KNOW SHE'S EVIL AND ALL,
BUT STILL.
SESSHOMARU SHOULD NEVER
HAVE USED HER LIKE THAT.
HOW TOTALLY MEAN.
OK, SO MAYBE IT WAS ME
WHO DREW YOUR FATHER'S SWORD,
BUT THE IMPORTANT THING IS
TO USE IT AGAINST YOUR BROTHER,
ESPECIALLY NOW THAT
HE'S TURNED INTO SOME
KIND OF GIANT DEMON DOG.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!