>> BETWEEN CATCHING A COLD AND
TRYING TO HELP SOTA WITH HIS
FIRST GIRLFRIEND, I'D SPENT A
LOT OF TIME BACK AT MY HOME.
BUT AT LAST, INUYASHA AND I HAVE
RETURNED TO THE FEUDAL ERA.
>> SEE YOU LATER, SOTA.
LET'S GO, KAGOME.
>> YOU BET!
>> THE SUSPICIOUS FAITH HEALER
AND THE BLACK KIRARA.
FINALLY, WE CAN GET BACK TO
TRACKING NARAKU.
WE SURE WASTED A LOT OF TIME ON
ALL THAT TRIVIAL JUNK.
>> WELL, EXCUSE ME.
I DIDN'T REALIZE JUST HOW
TRIVIAL MY COLD REALLY WAS.
>> UH...
>> OH, BOY.
WHAT A FOOL.
HE'S DIGGING HIS OWN
GRAVE AGAIN.
>> YEAH.
WHAT A DOOFUS.
>> OH, IT'S NOT HIS FAULT
HE'S A DIMWIT.
>> HMMPH!
>> SO, NARAKU DISAPPEARED IN THE
DIRECTION OF THE OX TIGER,
CORRECT?
THAT'S NORTHEAST, MEANING IT'S
IN THAT DIRECTION.
>> HA HA!
GOOD CALL, MIROKU.
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
LET'S GET GOING!
HA HA.
>> HUH?
>> JUST YOU WAIT, NARAKU.
I'LL FIND YOU!
>> STOP!
GET BACK HERE, INUYASHA!
[GROWLING]
>> HEAR ME OUT!
THE DIVINE ORACLE HAS BEEN
RECEIVED.
THE TWIN-TAIL INVITES CALAMITY!
>> TWIN-TAIL?!
YOU MEAN THE CAT?
>> IT IS SAID THAT WHEN A CAT'S
TAIL BECOMES TWO, IT POSSESSES
SUPERNATURAL POWERS.
YOU MUST EXPEL THE TWIN-TAIL
FROM THE VILLAGE OR THERE IS
SURE TO BE MISFORTUNE.
[GROANS]
HA HA HA HA HA!
AGH!
OOF!
YOU'LL DO WELL TO STAY OUT OF
THIS VILLAGE.
DAMN YOU TO HELL, CURSED
TWIN-TAIL!
>> KURORO!
KURORO!
KURORO?
KURORO?!
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING, KIRARA?
KIRARA?
OH!
WHERE DID SHE GET TO NOW?
KIRARA!
HEY, KIRARA!
OH.
OOH.
WHOA!
[GRUNTING]
MUCH BETTER.
>> KURORO?
>> HUH?
>> OH.
WHAT A CUTE GIRL.
SO, THAT'S WHAT YOU WERE
FOLLOWING, KIRARA,
THE SOUND OF HER VOICE.
>> KURORO.
SO, THIS IS WHERE YOU ARE.
I WAS SO WORRIED.
>> HUH?
>> HERE, KITTY, COME ON.
THAT'S MY GIRL.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
HA!
I'M SO GLAD I FOUND YOU, KURORO.
>> AHEM.
THAT IS NOT KURORO.
HER NAME IS KIRARA.
>> LET'S PUT THIS COLLAR ON.
>> KIRARA IS SANGO'S PARTNER.
HUH?
>> THERE.
IT'S ON.
NOW, LET'S GO HOME, KURORO.
>> I TOLD YOU!
THAT'S NOT KURORO!
THE NAME'S KIRARA!
>> HUH?
[GASPS]
IT'S THE VILLAGERS AGAIN.
RUN AWAY, KURORO.
QUICKLY!
DON'T LET THE MEN CAPTURE YOU.
>> I KEEP TELLING HER IT'S
KIRARA.
SHE'S CUTE BUT KIND
OF A STRANGE GIRL.
[GROWLS]
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU,
KIRARA?
>> LOOK OVER THERE.
THAT CAT AGAIN!
>> I THOUGHT WE CHASED IT FAR
AWAY FROM THE VILLAGE.
[GRUMBLING]
[SNARLING]
>> LET'S GET IT!
HERE!
>> GET OUT OF HERE!
>> STOP IT!
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING!
[GRUNTING]
NO, KIRARA!
YOU MUSTN'T BEAR YOUR FANGS
AGAINST HUMANS.
>> HEY, SHIPPO, WHAT'S WRONG?!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> OH, THANK GOODNESS.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
ARE YOU IN LEAGUE WITH THAT
DEMON CAT?
>> WHO ARE YOU CALLING
A DEMON CAT?!
>> COME, COME NOW, INUYASHA.
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
>> I THINK I'D BETTER HANDLE
THIS.
[GROWLING]
VILLAGERS, VIOLENCE NEVER SOLVED
ANYTHING.
I'M SURE WE CAN TALK THINGS OUT.
WHY YOU--
>> HEY, SETTLE DOWN.
>> THIS ISN'T VERY MONKISH
OF YOU.
>> HUH?
>> STOP, YOU MEN!
STOP THAT AT ONCE!
PLEASE, DON'T DO ANYTHING
VIOLENT.
CATS ARE VENGEFUL CREATURES AND
WILL CURSE YOU FOR 7
GENERATIONS.
BESIDES, THAT CAT IS NOT KURORO.
>> HUH?
>> OH, DEAR.
THE VILLAGERS HAVE BEEN AWFULLY
RUDE TO YOU.
>> NEVER MIND THAT.
TELL US, THOUGH,
WHAT'S ALL THE FUSS OVER ONE
LITTLE CAT?
>> WELL, IT IS NOT THAT SIMPLE.
>> I WONDER WHO THAT GIRL WAS.
KIRARA SURE SEEMED TO LIKE HER.
SHE MUST HAVE A KIND HEART.
I BET SHE DOES.
>> A SMART CAT NAMED KURORO
LIVED IN THIS VILLAGE.
SHE USED TO PLAY OFTEN WITH THE
CHILDREN OF THE VILLAGE, BUT
SEVERAL DAYS AGO, A VERY
IMPORTANT FAITH HEALER PASSED
THROUGH THE VILLAGE AND FOUND
OUT ABOUT OUR FRIEND THE CAT,
AND HE READ AN ORACLE THAT SAID
THAT THE TWIN-TAIL WAS BAD LUCK,
AND HE COMMANDED US TO EXPEL IT
FROM THE VILLAGE.
>> I SEE.
THAT'S WHY THE VILLAGE GIRL
MISTOOK KIRARA FOR KURORO.
>> I FEEL BADLY FOR THE
CHILDREN, BUT WE CANNOT AFFORD
TO HAVE ANY CALAMITY HIT OUR
VILLAGE.
>> PRETTY HARSH, KICKING A POOR
CAT OUT OF THE VILLAGE.
>> SOMETHING SOUNDS FISHY ABOUT
THAT FAITH HEALER.
>> I TEND TO AGREE.
I THINK WE BETTER PAY THAT MAN A
VISIT.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
HUH?
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU,
SHIPPO?
>> WELL, I THINK MAYBE ALL
THIS RICH FOOD IS GIVING
THE LITTLE GUY A BELLYACHE.
>> I WONDER WHERE I CAN FIND
THAT CUTE GIRL I SAW DOWN BY THE
RIVER.
[SIGHS]
>> KURORO!
>> OH!
I KNOW THAT VOICE!
UH...
THAT'S THE SAME GIRL!
>> KURORO!
KURORO.
[GRUNTING]
HUH?
>> HEY!
I THINK THIS IS YOURS.
>> HMM?
>> MY NAME'S SHIPPO.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU THAT
WASN'T YOUR KURORO THAT YOU PUT
THIS COLLAR ON, IT WAS KIRARA.
>> HUH?
KIRARA?
>> YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A CAT
NAMED KURORO, RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> I'D BE GLAD TO HELP YOU
LOOK FOR HER.
>> THANKS.
MY NAME IS KOUME.
>> KOUME?
OH, THAT'S PRETTY.
>> OHM, KITTY, KITTY KIARO.
FERRUN KUCKUAPORA.
OHM, KITTY, KITTY KIARO.
>> DAMN THAT SHIPPO.
WHERE'D HE GO?!
>> HE WAS SURE ACTING STRANGE.
>> HEY, YOU GUYS,
LOOK UP THERE!
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> AN OMINOUS DEMONIC AURA.
>> IT'S THAT FAITH HEALER.
THERE'S SOMETHING EVIL ABOUT
HIM.
>> LET'S HURRY.
ACCORDING TO THE HEAD MAN, THE
FAITH HEALER IS IN THE SHRINE
JUST OUTSIDE THE VILLAGE.
>> RIGHT.
>> KURORO!
KURORO!
KURORO.
AGH!
SHIPPO.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE'S AROUND
HERE.
>> HMM.
>> WOW.
YOU REALLY CARED FOR THIS CAT,
I CAN TELL.
>> MMM.
YEAH, 'CAUSE...
KURORO'S GOING TO HAVE A LITTER
OF KITTENS SOON.
>> SHE IS?
SHE'S GOING TO BE OK.
I PROMISE I WILL HELP YOU FIND
HER, KOUME.
>> MMM.
MM-HMM.
>> COME ON, LET'S GO FURTHER
INTO THE FOREST.
[WIND HOWLS]
I DON'T LIKE THE LOOKS OF THAT.
[GASP]
>> AAGH!
>> FOX MAGIC TOP!
[GRUNTS]
HERE!
HANG ONTO ME!
WE'LL HAVE TO GET TO HIGHER
GROUND!
>> HUH?
WHAT'S OVER THERE?
RATS!
A HUGE ARMY OF RATS!
[SCREAMING]
>> HMM?
WHAT'S THIS?
[GASPS]
RATS!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
OUR SACRED SCROLL!
>> HA HA HA HA!
FOOLISH VILLAGERS!
NOT A SIGN OF THE FRIGHTFUL
TWIN-TAIL IN THE VILLAGE!
WHILE THE CAT'S AWAY,
THE RATS WILL PLAY--
AND DEVOUR EVERYTHING IN SIGHT!
AH HA HA HA HA!
[PANTING]
>> I CAN'T GO MUCH FURTHER!
HUH?
IT'S KIRARA!
>> KURORO!
THAT'S KURORO!
>> YOUR CAT HAS TWO TAILS ALSO!
>> OH, YOU CAME FOR ME!
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> JUST AS WE THOUGHT.
THE DEMONIC AURA CREATED A
BARRIER.
>> WHICH MEANS...
THE FAITH HEALER IS A DEMON IN
DISGUISE.
>> WELL, I AIN'T STANDING FOR
THAT!
I'LL BREAK THROUGH THAT STINKING
BARRIER!
TETSUSAIGA!
AARGH!
HA.
THAT SHOULD DO IT.
[RUMBLING]
HUH?
[LAUGHING]
FINALLY SHOWING YOURSELF, HUH,
RAT DEMON?
>> HMM.
I SEE THAT YOU'RE ACTUALLY A
HALF DEMON.
HOW DARE YOU, A HALF DEMON, DEFY
THE GREAT TESSO.
>> I'LL SHOW YOU HOW!
[SNARLS]
>> THE FELINE!
>> HEY!
HE MAY BE LARGE, BUT HE'S STILL
FEARS CATS.
>> NO WONDER YOU HATED THE CAT
THAT ALL THE VILLAGE CHILDREN
LOVED SO MUCH.
>> THAT'S ALL THE INFORMATION I
NEED.
I'M TAKING YOU OUT, RAT!
WIND SCAR!
[SNARLS]
HA.
SHOULD HAVE KNOWN HE WAS NOTHING
BUT TALK.
HUH?
>> HA HA HA HA HA.
IS THAT THE EXTENT OF YOUR
SO-CALLED POWER, HALF DEMON?
>> WIND SCAR WON'T WORK ON HIM.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
PARALYZED WITH FEAR?!
>> HARDLY!
>> HOLD IT.
DON'T BE FOOLED.
THAT IS NOT THE DEMON'S TRUE
APPEARANCE.
>> IT'S NOT?
>> I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN HE'S A
DEMON CREATED BY THE DEMONIC
AURA OF THE OTHER RATS.
>> OH.
>> THE SWORD WILL PASS RIGHT
THROUGH WITHOUT DOING ANY
DAMAGE.
>> HUH?
THEN WHAT DO WE DO?
>> I CAN HANDLE THIS.
MY WIND TUNNEL SHOULD TAKE CARE
OF THAT RAT INSTANTLY.
[GRUNTS]
WHAT HAPPENED?!
>> HE COMPLETELY DISAPPEARED.
>> HE ESCAPED!
[PANTING]
>> KURORO, WHERE YOU TRYING TO
LEAD US TO?
[MEOWING]
[GASPS]
>> KURORO, YOUR KITTENS
ARE SAFE!
>> THAT'S TERRIFIC!
>> HMM!
LET'S GO BACK TO THE VILLAGE.
WE NEVER HAVE TO BE APART AGAIN,
KURORO.
[LAUGHING]
>> I CAN SMELL IT!
I CAN SMELL IT!
THE SCENT OF A HUMAN CHILD!
BY DEVOURING A SINGLE CHILD,
I'LL BE ABLE TO DOUBLE MY POWER!
>> A DEMONIC AURA!
[SNARLS]
>> KURORO!
>> YOU CAN'T GO OUT THERE,
KOUME!
IT'S WAY TOO DANGEROUS.
>> BUT I--
>> KURORO CAN HANDLE WHATEVER'S
OUT THERE.
SHE WANTS TO PROTECT THESE
KITTENS.
[SIGHS]
>> MM-HMM.
>> I FOUND HER!
[SNARLS]
YOU!
WHY MUST YOU KEEP INTERFERING?!
>> HUH?
>> KOUME, STAY HERE
AND DON'T MOVE A MUSCLE.
>> SHIPPO!
>> KURORO!
>> PERSISTENT CREATURE!
NOW YOU DIE!
AAGH!
RELEASE ME!
>> GOOD WORK, KURORO!
>> DAMN!
FEEL MY MAGIC RAT POWER!
>> OH, NO!
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
>> HMM?
HMM?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I'M OK.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE THE ENTRANCE
HAS BEEN SEALED.
>> DON'T WORRY, KOUME.
I'LL FIND A WAY TO GET
US OUT OF HERE.
HMM...
AH, THE EXIT HAS TO BE OVER
HERE.
[GRUNTING]
OH!
>> SHIPPO!
>> HUH?
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?!
[SIGHS]
[MEOWING]
>> DOES IT HURT?
>> YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'M IMMORTAL.
[GRUNTING]
>> THAT DAMN RAT.
I BET WE SCARED HIM, SO HE TOOK
OFF AND ESCAPED FROM THE
VILLAGE.
>> NOT LIKELY.
I DOUBT HE'D ABANDON THE VILLAGE
AFTER GOING THROUGH ALL THE
TROUBLE TO GET OF THE CAT.
>> THEN YOU THINK HE'S STILL
CLOSE BY?
>> YEAH, PROBABLY.
>> KURORO!
>> HMM?
>> IT'S THAT TWIN-TAIL,
SHE'S BACK AGAIN!
>> COME ON, LET'S GO.
>> YEAH!
>> WHERE IS SHE?
>> FLUSH HER OUT!
>> DON'T LET HER ESCAPE!
>> OUT, TWIN-TAIL!
[GRUNTING]
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> THAT'S THE COLLAR SHIPPO
WAS HOLDING BEFORE.
>> IS THIS THE CAT THE VILLAGERS
WERE TALKING ABOUT?
>> POOR LITTLE THING LOOKS
PRETTY BEAT UP.
HUH?
>> THAT CAT WANTS US
TO FOLLOW IT.
I THINK IT'S TRYING TO TAKE US
SOMEWHERE.
>> HUH.
[GRUNTING]
[MEOWING]
>> I CAN'T BREATH.
NO AIR.
WE'RE LOSING AIR.
>> I THINK I'M ALMOST TO THE
OTHER SIDE.
HOLD TIGHT, KOUME.
>> OK.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
>> JUST A BIT MORE.
I'M ALMOST THERE.
HOLD TIGHT, KOUME.
I'M ALMOST THERE!
[GRUNTING]
AAGH!
I DID IT!
KOUME, WE'RE THROUGH!
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
>> HUH?
>> A YOUNG LITTLE DEMON!
OUT OF MY WAY!
I KNOW THERE'S A HUMAN CHILD
INSIDE THAT CAVE.
MOVE AND LET ME DEVOUR HER!
>> NOT THIS TIME!
>> MOVE, YOU LITTLE BRAT!
>> THE SCRATCH HE GOT FROM
KURORO HAS VANISHED!
[GASPS]
INUYASHA!
>> HA!
EATING A HUMAN CHILD TO INCREASE
YOUR OWN DEMONIC POWER.
HOW REPULSIVE CAN YOU GET?
>> SILENCE, YOU!
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
YOUR HALF-DEMON TRICKS
DON'T WORK ON ME?
[PANTING]
>> HE'S AN ILLUSION!
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE SCRATCH!
>> HMM?
AN ILLUSION?!
NOW IT ALL MAKES SENSE.
THIS SHOULD WORK.
[GRUNTS]
INUYASHA, BEHIND HIM!
AIM FOR THAT ROCK THERE!
>> HUH? NO!
>> SO, THAT'S WHERE YOU'VE
HIDDEN YOUR TRUE SELF!
WIND SCAR!
[SCREAMING]
>> HE DID IT!
[SQUEALS]
>> HUH?
>> KURORO?!
[WHIMPERS]
KURORO!
>> YOU SHOULD BE PROUD.
KURORO IS EXTREMELY BRAVE.
SHE IGNORED HER OWN INJURIES TO
FIND US AND LEAD US TO YOU TWO.
>> KURORO!
THANK YOU SO MUCH, KURORO.
>> KOUME.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
>> WE'LL NEVER FORGET YOU!
>> YOU SAVED US!
>> BYE!
BYE!
>> TAKE CARE, KOUME.
[MEOWING]
>> COME ON, KITTIES.
TIME TO HAVE SOMETHING TO EAT.
WE'LL BE TOGETHER FOREVER
AND EVER...
KURORO.
>> SHIPPO,
LOOKS LIKE YOU DID PRETTY GOOD.
>> KOUME TOLD US HOW YOU SAVED
HER.
>> YEP, JUST DOING MY JOB,
PROTECTING A WOMAN IN TROUBLE.
>> A RESCUE MISSION WITH
NO ULTERIOR MOTIVES.
>> IT'S TOO BAD A CERTAIN MONK
NEVER PRACTICES WHAT HE
PREACHES.
>> HUH?!
>> HEY THERE, SHIPPO.
I'LL BET YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH
THAT LITTLE HUMAN GIRL.
>> NO WAY!
I WAS NOT!
>> YOU HAD A THING FOR HER!
>> DID NOT, DID NOT, DID NOT!
>> I MUST BE TRUE, OTHERWISE
YOU WOULDN'T BE SO MAD.
>> YOU'RE WRONG!
DON'T TEASE ME!
>> STUPID.
>> INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
>> SIT, BOY!
[GRUNTS]
>> WHY DOES SHE DO IT TO ME?
>> AH.
THAT'S BETTER.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> NO MISTAKE, THIS IS
THE SCENT OF THE HERBS
THAT URASUE WAS USING!
>> YOU MEAN THE DEMON WOMAN
WHO REINCARNATED KIKYO?
>> I CAN STILL PICK UP
KIKYO'S SCENT.
NO WAY!
KIKYO CAN'T BE MANIPULATING
URASUE'S SOLDIERS.
>> DON'T TELL ME THERE ARE
OTHERS ZOMBIE PUPPETS HERE
THAT POSSESS HUMAN SOULS.
NEXT TIME, "PLOT OF
THE WALKING DEAD."
>> URASUE IS SUPPOSED
TO BE DEAD!