THE SACRED JEWEL; SAID TO
GRANT ONE'S EVERY WISH.
IN ORDER TO SEARCH FOR THE
SHARDS OF THE SHATTERED JEWEL,
I BEGAN CROSSING BETWEEN THE
PRESENT AND THE FEUDAL ERA
THROUGH THE HIDDEN WELL IN MY
FAMILY'S SHRINE.
WHENEVER I CAN, I RETURN TO THE
PRESENT TO ATTEND CLASSES LIKE
ANY NORMAL JUNIOR HIGH STUDENT.
I'VE GOT TO STUDY AND TRY TO GET
THROUGH MY TESTS, AFTER ALL.
NONE OF MY SCHOOL FRIENDS KNOW
ABOUT MY DOUBLE LIFE.
THEN AGAIN, I KIND OF DOUBT
THEY'D BELIEVE ME EVEN IF
I TOLD THEM.
OH, NO.
I DON'T GET THIS.
I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
[SIGHS]
>> ALL RIGHT.
TIME'S UP.
>> WHAT A DISASTER.
I WAS SO CONFIDENT ABOUT MY
HISTORY TEST--ESPECIALLY SINCE
IT WAS ON THE FEUDAL ERA.
WHAT A SHOCKER.
>> COME ON, CHEER UP, WILL YOU,
KAGOME?
>> REALLY, WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
YOU'VE BEEN AWAY SO MUCH LATELY.
>> OH, I'LL HAVE TO RETAKE IT.
>> WANT ME TO TAKE THE MAKEUP
TEST WITH YOU, KAGOME?
>> HI THERE, KAGOME.
YOU MADE IT TO SCHOOL TODAY.
SO, ARE YOU FEELING ANY BETTER?
>> OH, HEY THERE, HOJO.
>> HEY, KAGOME, YOU WON'T
BELIEVE WHAT I FOUND.
>> HUH?
WHAT'S THIS?
>> IT'S A SCROLL OF THE HOJO
FAMILY TREE.
>> IT'S LONG.
>> AND...HERE.
LOOK AT THE WIFE'S NAME OF MY
ANCESTOR AKITOKI HOJO, WHO
LIVED 500 YEARS AGO DURING
THE FEUDAL ERA.
>> HIS WIFE?
FOR REAL?
>> SEE?
>> IT SAYS KAGOME.
NO WAY, THAT CAN'T BE.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
>> HE'S RIGHT.
THAT'S MY NAME ON THE HOJO
FAMILY TREE.
>> WOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT ONE OF
HOJO'S ANCESTOR'S IS ACTUALLY
NAMED KAGOME HOJO.
>> IF KAGOME BREAKS UP WITH THAT
NO-GOOD BOYFRIEND OF HERS AND
HOOKS UP WITH HOJO, HER NAME
WOULD BE KAGOME HOJO, TOO!
>> MAYBE THAT'S NOT JUST
A FAMILY TREE,
BUT A FORTUNE-TELLING SCROLL.
>> I BET HOJO'S THINKING
THE SAME THING HIMSELF.
>> SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
IT, KAGOME?
>> OH, WELL.
I BETTER BRUSH UP ON HISTORY
AGAIN.
>> GUESS SHE'S NOT IN THE MOOD
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
>> OH, THAT REMINDS ME.
I BROUGHT THE PICTURES I TOOK
AT THE CULTURAL FESTIVAL.
>> HUH?
PICTURES?
>> SEE?
>> WOW, NICE SHOTS.
>> YOU SAID IT.
KAGOME LOOKS GREAT.
>> OH, NO.
THAT'S A REAL DEMON IN THE
PICTURE!
>> HEY, MISTER, DROP YOUR
BELONGINGS AND GET OUT OF HERE.
>> HUH?
>> DO IT FAST BEFORE YOU WIND UP
GETTING HURT.
>> HAND OVER YOUR MONEY AND YOUR
VALUABLES.
>> YOU'LL NEVER MAKE FRIENDS
WITH THAT ATTITUDE.
YOU SOUND EXACTLY LIKE BANDITS
BOSSING ME AROUND.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE WE ARE
BANDITS, YOU IDIOT!
>> STOP ACTING SO DENSE AND HAND
OVER THE MONEY!
>> AH--
>> WHAT, GOT YOURSELF INTO
TROUBLE AGAIN?
>> WHO THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE?
UGH!
>> WAIT, I KNOW YOU.
>> HEY, YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD,
AKITOKI.
>> MY OLD FRIENDS, SHIPPO
AND INUYASHA!
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO MY
RESCUE.
>> OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
HAVE SOME.
>> PICKLED PLUMS?
>> TRY ONE.
I HEAR THEY'RE GOOD FOR YOUR
HEALTH.
>> SO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING WAY
OUT HERE, ANYWAY?
>> OH, RIGHT.
IT'S A LONG STORY, SO I'LL
EXPLAIN IT LATER.
FIRST I NEED TO ASK SOMETHING
OF THE PRIESTESS KAEDE.
>> WHAT, OLD KAEDE?
>> WHY DO YOU WANT TO TALK
TO HER?
>> OH.
SO YOU'RE ON SOME KIND OF
MISSION THEN, ARE YOU, AKITOKI?
>> I AM.
IT'S ABOUT SOMETHING CALLED
KENKON, THE NAGINATA OF HEAVEN
AND EARTH.
THE NAGINATA IS A DEMONIC WEAPON
WHICH HAS A BLADE AFFIXED
TO EITHER END.
>> A DEMONIC WEAPON?
>> RECENTLY, THE HOJO FAMILY HAS
BEEN PLAGUED WITH TERRIBLE
MISFORTUNE, AND THE SOURCE OF
THIS MISFORTUNE IS SUPPOSEDLY
THE BLADE, NAGINATA OF HEAVEN
AND EARTH.
>> HMM.
INCREDIBLE.
>> A DEMONIC AURA.
>> HOW OMINOUS.
>> LOOK AT INUYASHA.
PUT IT AWAY.
>> YES, UH, OF COURSE.
>> INUYASHA--
>> HEY, SNAP OUT OF IT!
WAKE UP!
>> HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> THE SWORD WAS STARTING TO
POSSESS YOU.
>> WE WERE TOLD AN EXORCISM WAS
NECESSARY TO DISPERSE THE
DEMONIC AURA FROM AROUND THIS
WEAPON, BUT AS YOU WITNESSED,
THE POWER OF THE BLADE IS
TOO STRONG.
SO, IT WAS DECIDED THAT SOMEONE
SHOULD JOURNEY TO MOUNT HAKUREI
TO PURIFY IT, AND I WAS THE ONE
WHO WAS CHOSEN TO DO SO.
>> BUT THAT MOUNTAIN ISN'T THERE
ANYMORE.
>> I KNOW.
NOT LONG AGO, A NATURAL DISASTER
CAUSED THE MOUNTAIN TO COLLAPSE,
LEAVING NOT A TRACE OF ITS
FORMER GLORY OR ITS POWERS OF
PURIFICATION.
>> HMM.
>> IF THE BLADE CANNOT BE
PURIFIED, THE HOJO FAMILY WILL
CONTINUE TO BE PLAGUED WITH
ILL FORTUNE.
>> SO, YOU CAME TO ME IN SEARCH
OF ANOTHER SOLUTION FOR THIS
TROUBLESOME BLADE OF YOURS?
>> I WAS TOLD TO SEEK OUT YOUR
ADVICE.
THEY SAID THAT IF ANYONE WOULD
HAVE AN ANSWER, IT'D BE YOU.
>> IT'S THAT PEAK.
DEEP IN THE WOODS OF THAT
MOUNTAIN, YOU'LL FIND THE SACRED
SHRINE OF FURAI.
IF YOU SURRENDER THE BLADE TO
THAT SHRINE, THE DEMONIC AURA
SHOULD DISSIPATE BY ITSELF.
>> THE SHRINE OF FURAI?
>> IT IS THE HOLIEST PLACE
I KNOW OF AROUND THESE PARTS.
>> BUT WHERE EXACTLY IS DEEP IN
THE WOODS OF THE MOUNTAIN?
HOW CAN WE POSSIBLY FIND IT?
>> A RIVER FLOWS TO THE EAST
OF THE HIGHEST PEAK.
IF YOU FOLLOW IT UPRIVER,
YOU WILL COME UPON THE SHO'UN
WATERFALL, AND FURAI SHRINE IS
APPARENTLY NOT FAR AWAY.
>> SHO'UN WATERFALL.
FRIENDS, WILL YOU HELP ME MAKE
THIS IMPORTANT JOURNEY?
>> HA, YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
>> I WAS ACCOSTED BY ROBBERS
EARLIER TODAY, AND EVER SINCE
I'VE HAD POSSESSION OF THAT
BLADE, BAD THINGS HAVE KEPT
HAPPENING TO ME.
PLEASE, WON'T YOU HELP ME?
>> AKITOKI IS STILL MY VASSAL.
IT'S A MASTER'S RESPONSIBILITY
TO COME TO THE RESCUE OF HIS
SERVANTS.
>> KAGOME SHOULD GO WITH YOU.
SHE'LL BE RETURNING SHORTLY.
>> OH, KAGOME WILL BE COMING ON
OUR JOURNEY?
>> OH, DEAR.
>> SIS, ARE YOU SURE YOU HAVE
EVERYTHING?
>> YEP, I'M TAKING MY TEXTBOOK
SO I'LL BE ABLE TO STUDY ON THE
OTHER SIDE, TOO.
I'M ALL SET.
>> MAYBE THIS TIME I'LL SAY YOU
HIT YOUR HEAD ON SOMETHING AND
HAVE TEMPORARY AMNESIA.
>> GRAMPS, AMNESIA MIGHT BE
A LITTLE EXTREME, I THINK.
[MEOWS]
>> BUYO.
THAT'S IT.
I'LL SAY YOU HAVE A CAT ALLERGY.
>> OR YOU WERE PARALYZED BY A
VOODOO DOLL THAT WAS SENT TO US
FOR PURIFICATION.
>> SORRY I'M LATE.
KAGOME, I BROUGHT YOU SOME
LUNCH.
>> UH, IT'S SO HEAVY.
SURE YOU MADE ENOUGH?
>> YOU CAN SHARE IT WITH YOUR
FRIENDS.
>> THANKS, MOM.
I'M SURE THEY'LL LOVE IT.
I BETTER GET GOING.
>> TAKE CARE NOW.
>> SO, WHICH IS IT?
CAT ALLERGY OR VOODOO?
>> NEITHER, THANK YOU.
>> OH...
>> WHERE ARE YOU, KAGOME?
KAGOME?
OH, I WISH YOU WOULD HURRY UP
AND GET HERE.
>> AH!
UGH.
[GROANING]
AAH!
>> YOU'RE HOJO'S ANCESTOR,
AKITOKI HOJO.
SORRY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YES.
DON'T EVEN MENTION IT.
>> HERE YOU GO.
THE NINJA FOOD I PROMISED YOU.
>> VIETNAMESE FLAVOR?
>> I FOUND SOME STUFF YOU
HAVEN'T TRIED YET.
HEY, WHERE'S INUYASHA?
>> HE'S SULKING.
>> HUH?
>> HE DOESN'T WANT TO HELP
AKITOKI 'CAUSE IT WILL HOLD UP
THE SEARCH FOR THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS.
SOMETIMES THAT GUY IS SO
SELFISH.
>> INUYASHA?
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> IS IT TRUE THAT YOU'RE
SULKING?
>> NO, WHAT GAVE YOU THAT IDEA?
>> HE'S TOTALLY SULKING.
KAEDE TOLD ME THE WHOLE STORY,
YOU KNOW.
HOJO IS IN TROUBLE,
AND HE NEEDS US.
SO WHAT'S WRONG WITH US HELPING
HIM A BIT?
>> AND WHAT ABOUT THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS?
YOU WANT TO JUST FORGET THEM AND
LET NARAKU FIND THEM FIRST?
>> NO, OF COURSE NOT.
HOJO WOULDN'T EVEN NEED OUR HELP
EXCEPT THAT MOUNT HAKUREI WAS
DESTROYED, SO NOW HE CAN'T CARRY
OUT HIS MISSION.
DON'T YOU FEEL FOR THE GUY?
>> IT'S NARAKU'S FAULT THE
MOUNTAIN COLLAPSED, NOT MINE.
>> YEAH, BUT YOU CAN'T JUST TURN
YOUR BACK ON SOMEONE IN TROUBLE.
>> YOU'RE TOO NICE TO PEOPLE.
THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM.
>> HE'S RIGHT, KAGOME IS SUCH
A KIND PERSON.
>> HMM?
>> UHH--AAH!
>> YOU SPYING--
>> UGH!
>> I'LL TAKE YOU TO THE SHRINE
OR WHATEVER, BUT ONLY BECAUSE
KAGOME ASKED ME AS A FAVOR.
>> UH...
>> LET'S JUST HURRY AND GET THIS
OVER WITH.
>> OH, WHY DOES HE ALWAYS HAVE
TO BE SUCH A HARDHEAD?
[MEOWS]
>> YOU BE CAREFUL NOW, KAGOME,
AND THANKS FOR THE MEAL.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO YOUR
MOTHER'S COOKING.
MMM.
LOOKS DELICIOUS.
>> THAT MUST BE THE PLACE.
>> WE'LL MEET UP AT THE FOOT
OF THE MOUNTAIN, SHALL WE?
>> KIRARA, IT'S TIME TO GO.
[CHIRPS]
>> AH, IT TRANSFORMED!
>> COME ON, GET ON HER BACK.
>> ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ME?
WHAT ABOUT THE OTHERS?
>> I'LL BE GOING ALONG WITH
INUYASHA.
>> I'M WITH MIROKU.
HE'S PRETTY FAST.
>> QUIT DAWDLING.
LET'S MOVE.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU THERE.
>> WHOA, THEY'RE FAST.
>> COME ON, WE'D BETTER FOLLOW.
>> HUH?
>> UP YOU GO.
>> AAH!
>> HUH?
>> YAH.
>> REMEMBER, HANG ON TIGHT NOW.
>> RIGHT, I SURE WILL.
>> HEY, HOJO, ARE YOU OK
UP THERE?
>> YES.
JUST FINE.
LOOK AT HER.
KAGOME'S SMILE IS SO ADORABLE.
>> HOJO'S ANCESTOR, HUH?
THE NAME KAGOME WAS LISTED ON
THE FAMILY TREE SCROLL
HOJO SHOWED ME AT SCHOOL.
WHAT IF...
WHAT IF I COULDN'T RETURN TO THE
MODERN AGE AND ENDED UP MARRYING
THIS HOJO?
NAH.
>> HMM, LOOK, MIROKU, A RIVER.
>> HUH?
THAT MUST BE THE RIVER LADY
KAEDE TOLD US ABOUT THAT FLOWS
EAST OF THE MOUNTAIN.
>> HEY, AKITOKI, WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST THROW AWAY THE BLADE OR
LOSE IT SOMEHOW?
>> IF I DID THAT, THEN ANOTHER
FAMILY WOULD SUFFER MISFORTUNE.
I MUST HAVE IT PURIFIED.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
OOH.
>> YOU KNOW, HOJO, YOU'RE BRAVER
THAN I WOULD'VE FIGURED.
>> OH?
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
>> HOW COULD YOU BE SO MEAN,
INUYASHA?
>> THE GUY'S A WIMP.
HE SHOULD STOP ACTING SO BRAVE.
>> NOW YOU'RE REALLY BEING MEAN.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> MORE OR LESS.
>> THEY'RE FINALLY COMING.
>> HUH?
A TEA HOUSE.
MIROKU, THERE'S A TEA HOUSE UP
AHEAD.
>> THANK GOODNESS FOR THAT.
I COULD CERTAINLY USE A REST.
>> UGH.
[GROANING]
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> OH, NO.
LOOK AT MY SANDALS.
THEY'RE BOTH BROKEN.
YET ANOTHER BAD OMEN.
OH, THIS ACCURSED BLADE BRINGS
ME SO MUCH BAD LUCK.
>> ARGH.
WE'RE TAKING A BREAK ALREADY?
YOU HUMANS ARE SUCH A PAIN
TO BE WITH.
>> COME, COME, INUYASHA.
YOU CAN'T JUDGE US AGAINST YOUR
BRUTE STRENGTH.
WE'RE MADE OF DELICATE FLESH,
WE HUMANS.
>> HERE YOU ARE, DEAR.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THESE SWEET DUMPLINGS ARE
DELICIOUS.
>> TEA, YOUNG MAN?
>> YES, THANK YOU.
AAH!
>> HEY, WHAT HAPPENED?
HOLD ON.
>> HUH?
>> HERE YOU GO.
>> AHH.
AH, IT'S COLD.
>> GOTTA LOVE KAGOME WITH HER
BAG OF NINJA TRICKS.
>> KAGOME, WHAT EXACTLY IS THAT?
>> A COLD COMPRESS.
IT'S THE PERFECT THING FOR
COOLING DOWN A BURN.
>> OH, YES.
IT'S STARTING TO FEEL COOL
ALREADY.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
>> SEE?
HA HA.
>> WHOA, A LUNCH BOX!
>> WOW, THIS OMELET IS
DELICIOUS.
>> THE SIMMERED VEGETABLES ARE
EXCELLENT, TOO.
>> I LIKE THE NINJA FOOD WAY
BETTER.
THE KIND YOU ADD HOT WATER TO?
>> SIT, BOY.
>> NOW, IF YOU DON'T MIND--
NO, MY RICE BALL!
COME BACK!
>> HUH?
>> [GROANING]
THIS BLADE BRINGS ME SO MUCH
BAD LUCK.
UGH.
>> MERELY HAVING IT IN YOUR
POSSESSION BRINGS MISFORTUNE,
HUH?
>> EXACTLY, YOU'VE SEEN IT WITH
YOUR OWN EYES.
>> WELL, IT'S TRUE YOU'VE BEEN
HAVING A LOT OF ACCIDENTS
LATELY.
>> PERHAPS IT'S A COINCIDENCE.
>> NO, THIS ISN'T JUST A STRING
OF ACCIDENTS.
THE BLADE REALLY DOES BRING
MISFORTUNE TO WHOMEVER
POSSESSES IT.
>> ONE BIT OF BAD LUCK FOLLOWED
BY ANOTHER.
>> I GUESS IT WOULD BE HARD
TO TAKE AFTER AWHILE.
>> THE ONLY ISSUE HERE IS THAT
DEMONIC BLADE.
HUMANS SHOULDN'T POSSESS IT.
HE SHOULD JUST THROW IT AWAY.
>> NOT THIS AGAIN.
HOJO IS DOING WHAT HE CAN.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S WEAK AND GETS
AIRSICK, HE'S DOING HIS BEST,
AND I FOR ONE WANT TO DO WHAT I
CAN TO HELP HIM OUT.
>> WHY ARE YOU DEFENDING HIM
SO MUCH?
>> I'M NOT!
>> DEMON BLADES CAN ONLY BE
HANDLED BY DEMONS OR
HALF-DEMONS, LIKE ME.
NOT BY HUMANS LIKE YOU GUYS.
>> HUH?
>> HUMANS SHOULDN'T GET INVOLVED
IN THINGS LIKE THIS.
YOU GUYS JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> HEY, WAIT, INUYASHA!
>> HERE.
GOTTA THINK OF YOUR HEALTH
BEFORE A BIG MISSION.
EAT UP, AKITOKI.
>> THANK YOU, SHIPPO.
I APPRECIATE IT.
I'LL TAKE THAT OFF YOUR HANDS.
HUH?
>> WHA--
>> AAH!
>> BOULDERS!
>> THEY'RE COMING RIGHT AT US!
>> JUST LEAVE 'EM TO ME.
YAH!
>> HMM, WHO COULD'VE PUSHED
THOSE TOWARD US?
>> HUH?
I SMELL SOMETHING.
>> [SNIFFING]
SMELLS LIKE EXPLOSIVES.
>> EXPLOSIVES?
>> LOOK, UP THERE.
>> IS IT A BIRD?
>> IT LOOKED MORE LIKE A KITE.
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN A KITE LIKE
THAT STRANGE THING.
>> HERE IT COMES.
>> HOJO, GET OUT OF THE WAY!
>> AAH!
>> YAH!
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
>> A SACRED ARROW.
>> DAMN IT ALL TO HELL.
>> WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE THE
ASSASSIN ESCAPED US.
>> SO THIS IS WHERE HE PUSHED
THE BOULDERS FROM.
NOW THE QUESTION IS, WHO DID IT?
SO, MIROKU, DO YOU THINK IT WAS
THE BLADE HE WAS AFTER?
>> I HAVE TO ADMIT, IT SEEMED
TO BE AKITOKI HE WAS TARGETING,
SO, PROBABLY.
>> THE BLADE BRINGS MISFORTUNE
TO WHOEVER POSSESSES IT.
>> THAT'S WHY I KEEP TELLING YOU
TO LOSE THE THING.
IF SOMEONE ELSE WANTS IT,
LET THEM HAVE IT.
>> NO, I WILL NOT.
IF THE ENEMY WANTS THIS BLADE,
THEN HE MUST ALREADY HAVE THE
KON BLADE IN HIS POSSESSION.
>> THE KON BLADE?
WHAT'S THAT?
>> THE NAGINATA OF HEAVEN AND
EARTH WAS SO TERRIBLY POWERFUL
THAT THE BLADE WAS DIVIDED
INTO TWO.
ONE WAS THE KEN BLADE, THE OTHER
THE KON BLADE.
THEY WERE SENT AWAY TO DISTANT
LANDS--ONE TO THE NORTH, AND ONE
TO THE SOUTH.
LEGEND HAS IT THAT ONE OF THE
BLADES WAS ENTRUSTED TO THE HOJO
FAMILY.
>> AND WHAT HAPPENS IF THE TWO
BLADES ARE JOINED?
>> SPECIFIC DETAILS WEREN'T
PASSED DOWN TO US.
[CAWING]
HUH?
>> THAT'S A CROW.
>> MASTER INUYASHA.
MASTER INUYASHA!
OH, AH!
>> HEY, IT'S MYOGA.
>> HOW I'VE MISSED YOU,
MASTER INUYASHA.
>> MYOGA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
>> FINE GREETING THAT IS.
I COME REGARDING SOMETHING
TOTOSAI TOLD ME AFTER
MOUNT HAKUREI WAS DESTROYED.
>> THAT HOLY MOUNTAIN KEPT MANY
THINGS SEALED UP INSIDE IT.
SOMETHING TELLS ME THAT WE
HAVEN'T SEEN THE LAST
OF THE NAGINATA OF KENKON WHICH
WAS LEFT BEHIND BY KAIJINBO.
>> TOTOSAI WAS QUITE WORRIED
ABOUT IT.
>> THE NAGINATA OF KENKON.
>> YOU MEAN IT WAS FORGED BY
THE DEMON KAIJINBO?
>> AND TOTOSAI SAID THAT HE
WANTS YOU TO BE THE ONE TO SEAL
IT UP.
THAT'S WHY I CAME IN SEARCH
OF YOU.
>> MAN, WHY DO I HAVE TO DO IT?
>> NO ONE BUT INUYASHA CAN
DO IT.
>> HE WANTED ME TO PASS ALONG
THAT MESSAGE, AS WELL.
>> HUH.
>> DON'T BE LIKE THAT,
MASTER INUYASHA.
SOMEONE IS AFTER THE BLADE, AND
IT'S NONE OTHER THAN THE LEADER
OF THE DEMON NINJAS, HOSHIYOMI.
>> DID YOU SAY DEMON NINJAS?
>> EXACTLY.
DEMON NINJAS ARE JUST AS THEY
SOUND.
DEMONS VERSED IN THE NINJA WAYS,
AND HOSHIYOMI IS THE ONE WHO
MADE KAIJINBO FORGE THE NAGINATA
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> SACRED ARROW?
>> YES, SIR!
>> HMM.
INTERESTING.
>> WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO REACH
FURAI SHRINE TOMORROW, KAGOME.
>> HMM.
HUH?
>> GUESS THEY DIDN'T LEARN THEIR
LESSON THE FIRST TIME.
>> THEY MUST BE AFTER
THE KEN BLADE.
>> HOJO, QUICKLY, RUN THIS WAY,
AND HURRY IT UP.
HOJO!
HOJO, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> KAGOME!
>> COME ON, WE GOTTA KEEP GOING!
AAH!
>> KAGOME!
>> AAH, KAGOME!
>> KAGOME, AKITOKI!
AAH!
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME!
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> SO, YOU'RE HOSHIYOMI.
THE GUY WHO'S AFTER THE
KEN BLADE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT IT FOR?
>> NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
I DON'T OWE YOU AN EXPLANATION.
>> CHASED BY 4 DEMON NINJAS WITH
TERRIFYING WEAPONS, HOJO AND
I END UP GETTING SEPARATED FROM
INUYASHA AND THE OTHERS.
>> I NEVER IMAGINED THAT THE TWO
OF US WOULD TRAVEL ALONE
TO FURAI SHRINE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WE'RE ALONE?
>> NEXT TIME: MOUNTAIN OF
DEMONS: SURVIVAL OF THE DUO.
>> MAYBE THIS IS WHAT YOU'D CALL
A FORTUNATE MISFORTUNE.