>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS
BETWEEN US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> SHIPPO GOES ON A FURIOUS
RAMPAGE.
OUR FIERCEST ENEMY IS ONE OF US.
INUYASHA VERSUS SHIPPO.
THEIR INEVITABLE, FATEFUL
BATTLE IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> A FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
"INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ON THE JOURNEY IN SEARCH OF
OUR ARCH-ENEMY NARAKU, WE GO TO
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT.
>> ADAMANT BARRAGE!
>> [GRUNTING]
CURSE YOU.
>> I CAN SHOOT THIS ARROW.
[GRUNT]
GO!
WE MANAGE TO PREVENT NARAKU
FROM TAKING THE FINAL SACRED
JEWEL SHARD.
BUT THEN NARAKU GOES AFTER KIKYO
AND USES RAT DEMONS TO TRY
TO LURE HER OUT OF HIDING IN
HOPES OF KILLING HER.
>> THAT KIKYO.
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT I'D
FINALLY LURED HER OUT.
>> THOSE SLUGS ARE DESTROYING
THE MAYOSE TREE.
>> KOHAKU!
GIVE ME THE SHRINE!
>> [GRUNTING]
[THINKING] THIS IS WHAT NARAKU
WOULD EXPECT ME TO DO--PROTECT
THE SHRINE, EVEN IF IT MEANT MY
DEATH.
>> KOHAKU, YOU HAVE TO WAKE UP.
>> WE MANAGED TO DESTROY THE
RATS, BUT SANGO IS BESIDE
HERSELF ABOUT KOHAKU'S
INVOLVEMENT IN THE EVIL PLOT.
>> [THINKING] SISTER...
[GRUNTING]
>> KOHAKU!
>> ANSWER TRUTHFULLY, SANGO.
DO YOU REGRET PROTECTING KOHAKU?
>> YES, I DO.
BUT IF I HADN'T PROTECTED HIM,
I THINK...
I THINK I WOULD REGRET IT MORE.
>> AND THAT'S FINE.
THAT IS SIMPLY THE WAY OF THE
HUMAN HEART.
>> NARAKU CONTINUES TO HIDE
HIMSELF.
BUT NOW, SOMETHING CRUCIAL
HAPPENS THAT COULD PROVIDE A
CLUE TO NARAKU'S WHEREABOUTS.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
WHO DARES TO DISTURB MY SLEEP?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> WHOA!
LET ME DOWN!
>> INUYASHA, HOW CAN YOU BE SO
CRUEL?
YOU CAN'T DO THAT TO SHIPPO.
>> YEAH, CRUEL AND UNUSUAL!
>> THE VILLAGER SAID THE DEMON
PLAGUING THIS PLACE IS A FOX,
RIGHT?
>> INUYASHA, I CAN UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU WANT TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS FOX DEMON MISTREATING
VILLAGERS, BUT THIS IS, UH...
>> YOUR SOLUTION IS A LITTLE
OVERSIMPLISTIC.
>> GET ME DOWN!
WHAT DID I DO TO DESERVE THIS?
>> JUST LET SHIPPO DOWN.
WE CAN WORK THIS OUT LATER.
>> NOT GONNA HAPPEN!
>> HUH?
>> [GROWL]
>> [SCREAMING]
HELP, INUYASHA!
>> [LAUGHTER]
YOU SEE THAT?
HE CAME TO RESCUE THE LITTLE
FOX, LIKE I THOUGHT.
>> NO, MORE LIKE TO EAT HIM!
>> HUH?
>> AAH!
HELP ME!
>> HUH.
I'LL TEAR THAT LAME EXCUSE FOR A
DEMON APART IN A SINGLE SHOT.
>> NO, DON'T DO IT.
WE MERELY WANTED YOU TO CALM IT
DOWN, NOT KILL IT!
>> [GRUNT]
>> STAY BACK OUT OF THE WAY,
INUYASHA.
THAT'S NO DEMON.
IT'S A FOX DEITY.
>> DEFINITELY.
EXCEPT IT'S BEEN BEWITCHED BY
SOMETHING.
>> SCENT BEADS!
>> [GROWL]
>> THEY'RE EFFECTIVE AGAINST
CREATURES WITH A KEEN SENSE OF
SMELL.
>> INCLUDING INUYASHA, FROM
THE LOOKS OF IT.
>> [COUGHING]
>> YAH!
>> [GROWL]
[ROAR]
>> IT CAME OFF.
GOT YA!
>> GREAT JOB, SANGO!
>> YEAH.
>> EXCUSE ME.
IS THE FOX DEITY UNHARMED?
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW, FOLKS.
THE DEMONIC AURA IS GONE.
IT WILL PROBABLY GO BACK TO
ITS SHRINE.
>> WHAT A RELIEF.
>> WE'LL PREPARE A FEAST IN
GRATITUDE.
PLEASE COME TO THE HEAD MAN'S
HOUSE.
YOUR FRIEND LOOKS LIKE HE COULD
USE SOME REST.
>> WE'LL GLADLY ACCEPT YOUR
HOSPITALITY.
>> HEY, YOU FORGETTING SOMEONE?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> LET ME DOWN!
REMEMBER ME, YOUR FOX BAIT?
>> SHIPPO, HURRY UP AND COME
DOWN FROM UP THERE OR WE'RE
LEAVING YOU BEHIND.
>> [THINKING] YOU'LL PAY FOR
THIS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR ALL
YOUR ASSISTANCE, FOLKS.
THAT FOX IS THE GUARDIAN DEITY
OF THIS REGION,
SO KILLING IT CERTAINLY
WASN'T AN OPTION.
PLEASE MAKE YOURSELVES AT HOME.
>> AHH.
OH, THANKS FOR THE YUMMY DINNER.
>> EXCUSE ME?
>> THIS FISH IS RIGHTFULLY MINE.
>> HE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR HIM, WE
WOULDN'T BE SITTING HERE
EATING.
HERE, SHIPPO.
YOU CAN HAVE SOME OF MINE, TOO.
>> YEAH!
>> HA.
>> IT'S STILL BOTHERING ME,
THOUGH, THAT PARASITE ON THE
FOX.
>> WHY?
YOU KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
>> YES.
IT'S A PARASITE CHRYSALIS,
AND IT'S NOT MUCH OF A DEMON ON
ITS OWN.
IT ATTACHES ITSELF TO A MORE
POWERFUL DEMON.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF ONE
ATTACHING ITSELF TO A GUARDIAN
DEITY BEFORE.
>> SHALL WE LOOK INTO IT?
>> HOLD ON A MINUTE.
>> HUH?
>> WE'RE LOOKING FOR NARAKU,
REMEMBER?
WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO HUNT DOWN
EVERY LITTLE DEMON THAT CROSSES
OUR PATH.
BESIDES, I'M ALREADY TICKED OFF
ENOUGH THAT WE DON'T HAVE ANY
LEADS ON WHERE TO FIND HIM.
>> YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE BEING
MAD IS SOMETHING NEW FOR YOU.
>> HE'S HOPELESS.
INUYASHA'S MADDER THAN USUAL
TODAY 'CAUSE HE WASN'T THE HERO
THAT TOOK DOWN THE DEMON.
IT'S SO OBVIOUS.
>> SHUT UP!
QUIT TALKING SO BIG!
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ME
ANYWAY?
>> HE HIT ME!
>> INUYASHA!
>> IT'S SHIPPO'S FAULT.
YOU HEARD WHAT HE SAID.
>> I'LL GET YOU.
JUST WAIT.
[THUMPING]
>> [THINKING] THE WIND IS SO
STRONG.
[THUMPING]
HUH? A BIRD?
AAH!
A PARASITE!
>> THE PARASITE CHRYSALIS.
IS IT STILL ALIVE?
>> DON'T EVER SNEAK UP ON ME
LIKE THAT!
>> IF YOU'RE SCARED, THEN SHUT
UP AND FAINT ALREADY.
>> [GRUNT]
WHAT?
HERE I THOUGHT THERE WAS ONLY
ONE OF THEM.
[GRUNTING]
HA. THAT WAS EASY ENOUGH.
>> INUYASHA.
>> OH, HI, KAGOME.
DID I WAKE YOU UP?
>> HAVE YOU SEEN SHIPPO?
I CAN'T FIND HIM ANYWHERE.
>> HUH?
HE SHOULD BE RIGHT INSIDE.
I JUST KNOCKED HIM OUT A MINUTE
AGO.
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA, BEHIND YOU.
>> HA HA HA!
>> WAIT, THOSE ARE MY SCENT
BEADS.
WHEN DID HE TAKE THEM?
>> MMM.
[GROANING]
>> INUYASHA!
HEY, SHIPPO!
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> A PARASITE CHRYSALIS.
>> SHIPPO'S BEEN POSSESSED.
>> WE HAVE TO GO AFTER HIM.
IT'S SERIOUS TROUBLE FOR A
LITTLE DEMON LIKE SHIPPO TO
BECOME POSSESSED BY THOSE
PARASITES.
KIRARA, LET'S FOLLOW SHIPPO.
>> BRING SHIPPO BACK SAFELY,
YOU GUYS.
>> WE WILL.
>> YOU HAVE OUR WORD.
>> DO YOU THINK SHIPPO'S GONNA
WREAK HAVOC ON THE VILLAGE LIKE
THE FOX DEITY DID EARLIER?
>> I'D SAY SO, YES.
HE WON'T BE ABLE TO RESIST THE
PARASITE.
HOLD ON, SHIPPO!
>> AAH!
>> PHEW. HUH?
>> HEH HEH HEH!
>> HE GAVE US THE SLIP.
>> [SHIPPO GRUNTING]
HEH HEH HEH.
I'LL PAY YOU BACK THIS TIME.
HA HA HA.
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
>> YOU STILL GROGGY?
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED.
THOSE SCENT BEADS ARE STRONG.
>> YOU STAY HERE AND TAKE CARE
OF INUYASHA.
MEANWHILE, WE'LL GO OUT AND TRY
AND FIND SHIPPO.
>> SURE, SOUNDS GOOD.
GOOD LUCK, MIROKU.
>> COME ON.
LET'S GO, KIRARA.
>> LOOKS LIKE THE FOX DEITY HAS
CALMED DOWN.
>> MEANING WE CAN GET BACK TO
WORK IN THE FIELDS.
>> [GRUNTING]
AAH!
>> ARE YOU OK?
>> [MOANING]
>> HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
IT'S LIKE SOMETHING HUGE WAS
DRAGGED AROUND THE FARMLAND.
[RUSTLING]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> [CHANTING]
HUH?
AAH!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HE GOT ME!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> AAH!
WHO DID THIS?
>> HUH?
>> [LAUGHING]
>> WHO IS THAT?
IS ANYONE OUT THERE?
>> [SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
SOMEBODY HELP ME!
>> OH, HELP ME, ANYONE!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> RUN, RUN, AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
>> THERE HE IS.
>> SHIPPO.
>> HA HA.
>> HUH?
AAH!
STICKY RICE?
>> MIROKU AND SANGO HAVEN'T COME
BACK YET.
>> A NEW DEMON HAS APPEARED.
>> WE NEED YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
TO HELP SLAY IT.
>> [GASP]
>> THIS TIME IT'S NOT A DEITY.
IT'S THE REAL THING.
>> YOU'VE GOTTA DESTROY IT.
>> JUST A MINUTE.
>> GET THE BOWS AND ARROWS.
>> WE HAVE SPEARS, TOO.
>> [ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
>> OH, THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WE HAVE TO FIND SHIPPO BEFORE
THE VILLAGERS DO.
THE VILLAGERS ARE FURIOUS THIS
TIME.
>> OH, GREAT.
MY HEAD FEELS LIKE IT'S GONNA
SPLIT WIDE OPEN.
>> YEAH, WELL, GET OVER IT.
WE HAVE TO FIND SHIPPO BEFORE
THE VILLAGERS FIND HIM, OR HE'S
IN TROUBLE.
>> OVER THERE!
>> HMM?
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE ALREADY TOO
LATE.
>> INUYASHA!
>> ALL RIGHT, QUIT BUGGING ME.
>> DON'T LET IT GET AWAY!
>> PLEASE, STOP!
>> CALM DOWN, KAGOME.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
>> THAT'S SHIPPO'S DOUBLE UP
THERE.
>> [CHITTERING]
>> [GRUNT]
>> HA.
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE THE LITTLE
GUY'S GONNA GIVE UP THIS FIGHT
SO EASILY.
>> WE HAVE TO GET TO SHIPPO
BEFORE THE VILLAGERS DO ANY HARM
TO HIM.
>> [CLUCKING]
>> HUH?
>> MMM...
SHIPPO!
>> HEH HEH HEH.
HOW CLEVER OF YOU TO RECOGNIZE
ME.
>> QUIT YOUR YAPPING AND COME ON
DOWN HERE.
>> I'LL TAKE THAT PARASITE
CHRYSALIS OFF YOUR BACK.
>> [GROWL]
YOU LITTLE!
>> HEH HEH.
TAKE THIS--FOX FIRE!
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
LIKE YOUR FOX FIRE WOULD WORK ON
ME.
>> SMASHING TOP!
>> FIRST FOX FIRE AND NOW IT'S
THE SMASHING TOP.
I CAN SEE RIGHT THROUGH YOUR FOX
MAGIC, SHIPPO.
>> INUYASHA!
>> HUH? HUH?
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HEH HEH.
>> AAH!
>> I STILL HAVE A FEW TRICKS UP
MY SLEEVE.
>> YOU TWERP.
YOU WANT TO PLAY, DO YOU?
FINE.
BUT YOUR TRICKS WON'T WORK ON
ME.
>> INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA!
COME ON, SHIPPO.
INUYASHA!
[PANTING]
[THINKING] OH, THIS IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> THIS IS WHAT I CALL A STICKY
SITUATION.
>> PESKY SHIPPO.
HE'S TOUGHER THAN WE THOUGHT.
>> HUH?
>> [GROWL]
>> INUYASHA, IT'S YOU.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> DO ME A FAVOR.
DON'T ASK.
>> [PANTING]
>> KAGOME?
>> HEY, YOU GUYS.
SHIPPO GOT AWAY ON US AGAIN.
>> HOW TROUBLESOME.
ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING WE
CAN'T BE TOO ROUGH ON HIM.
>> HA. WHAT'S THE POINT IN
HOLDING BACK?
I'LL WAKE HIM UP WITH 50 OR 60
WHACKS ON THE HEAD.
>> 50 OR 60 TIMES IS A LITTLE
OVERBOARD.
>> DON'T EVEN TALK ABOUT SUCH
VIOLENT THINGS.
>> SANGO, WHAT ARE THOSE
DUMPLINGS FOR?
>> THEY CONTAIN PARALYSIS
POTION.
>> YOU'RE WAY MORE VIOLENT THAN
I AM.
>> TA DA!
HEH HEH HEH.
[GULP]
>> IS THE POISON WORKING?
>> AAH!
>> I'VE GOT YOU THIS TIME.
[GROWL]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> CHESTNUTS?
>> OH, NO.
SHIPPO'S GONNA GET AWAY ON US
AGAIN.
>> [GROWL]
>> HUH?
>> HMM.
>> INUYASHA!
>> I'LL KILL YOU!
YOU'RE DEAD!
>> TRAITOR!
YOU'D KILL ONE OF YOUR FRIENDS?
>> YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR MIND IF YOU
THINK I'LL GO EASY ON YOU JUST
'CAUSE YOU'RE A LITTLE KID!
>> AAH!
>> HUH?
>> IT BROKE AWAY.
>> AAH! UGH!
>> YOU OK, SHIPPO?
>> SHIPPO!
AH. THANK GOODNESS.
YOU'RE NOT HURT?
>> WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
>> HE WAS POSSESSED BY THE
PARASITE CHRYSALIS.
IT WASN'T HIS FAULT.
>> YEAH, WHAT SHE SAID.
>> HUH. OH, YEAH?
YOU DON'T SAY.
YOU SURE AGREE WITH HER FAST.
I'M BETTING YOU REMEMBER
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED WHILE
YOU WERE POSSESSED.
THOUGHT SO.
I WAS STARTING TO WONDER WHY YOU
KEPT COMING AFTER ME ALL THE
TIME.
>> SHUT UP!
THIS IS YOUR FAULT FOR ALWAYS
STICKING YOUR NOSE IN OTHER
PEOPLE'S BUSINESS!
>> YOU LITTLE--
SO, YOU DO REMEMBER EVERYTHING.
>> HMM?
>> OK, THAT'S ENOUGH.
>> WE'RE GOING AFTER THE
PARASITE THAT GOT AWAY.
>> YOU THINK IT'S LOOKING FOR A
NEW HOST TO LATCH ON TO, SANGO?
>> YES, SO LET'S STOP IT FROM
FINDING ANOTHER VICTIM.
>> HMM.
WHAT IS ALL THIS?
>> [GASP]
ANY IDEA WHAT'S GOING ON,
SANGO?
>> THESE PARASITE CHRYSALIS
USUALLY LATCH ONTO DEMONS THAT
ARE MUCH BIGGER THAN THEM, BUT
WITH SO MANY OF THEM HERE, THE
MOST REASONABLE EXPLANATION
WOULD BE THAT THEIR HOST HAS
DIED.
>> IN ANY CASE, WE BETTER DEAL
WITH THEM.
WIND TUNNEL!
>> HMM.
>> [THINKING] PARASITE
CHRYSALIS.
STRANGE.
I'VE SEEN SO MANY OF THEM
LATELY.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, SANGO?
THE PARASITES HAVE ALL BEEN
DESTROYED.
>> IS SOMETHING STILL BOTHERING
YOU?
>> WELL, JUDGING FROM THE NUMBER
OF PARASITES WE SAW, THE HOST
DEMON MUST HAVE BEEN PRETTY
ENORMOUS TO SUPPORT ALL OF THEM.
A REASONABLE EXPLANATION WOULD
BE THAT THE HOST HAS DIED,
BUT...
>> THE TROUBLE IS, WE DIDN'T
FIND THE REMAINS OF A LARGE
DEMON.
>> OR ITS SCENT.
>> WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
>> IF THEIR HOST DIDN'T DIE,
THEN WHAT?
>> THE HOST COULDN'T STAY HERE
ANYMORE.
>> WAIT, SANGO.
YOU AREN'T THINKING...
THAT NARAKU HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THESE PARASITES, ARE YOU?
>> I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
IT'S JUST NOT NORMAL.
>> [THINKING] YOU SAID IT.
SOMETHING'S DEFINITELY NOT
RIGHT.
>> [LAUGHTER]
>> [MUSIC]
>> KIKYO IS CLOSING IN ON THE
SECRET OF NARAKU'S IMMORTAL BODY
WHEN SHE FALLS INTO HIS TRAP.
>> WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN SINCE
MOUNT HAKUREI, KIKYO?
I'VE MISSED YOU.
>> I DIDN'T NOTICE HIM BEHIND
ME.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
>> OH, NO YOU DON'T, NARAKU.
I'M THE GUY WHO'S GONNA TAKE YOU
ON.
>> FATE BRINGS KIKYO, NARAKU,
INUYASHA, AND THE REST OF US
TOGETHER ONCE AGAIN.
NEXT TIME, THE ULTIMATE KEY TO
DEFEATING NARAKU.
>> INUYASHA, THERE'S BUT ONE WAY
TO DESTROY NARAKU.