>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS
BETWEEN US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> KOHAKU, WHO PROTECTS THE
SOURCE OF THE DEMON RATS,
FINALLY COMES TO A DECISION.
INUYASHA RUSHES TO HELP THE
SIBLINGS, WHO PREPARE TO
BATTLE EACH OTHER.
AND WHO SUDDENLY APPEARS BUT
KIKYO?
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> A FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
"INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> SO YOU LET YOUR FOLLOWERS EAT
THE MEAT OF THEIR PREY, AND THEN
DEVOUR THE BONES YOURSELF.
YOU ARE ZUSHI NEZUMI, RIGHT?
>> I'LL SEE THAT YOU'RE
REUNITED WITH THE OTHERS.
[ROARS]
>> WELL, IT SEEMS YOU'RE QUITE
SKILLED, KOHAKU.
TAKE THAT LITTLE SHRINE FROM THE
CREATURE'S BACK.
>> YES. UNH!
>> BY THE WAY, IF IT OPENS
ACCIDENTALLY, YOU'LL DIE.
[CHITTERING]
[HAKUDOUSHI LAUGHING]
THEY JUST KEEP COMING, DON'T
THEY?
THE RATS WILL SCATTER
EVERYWHERE, AND THEY'LL DEVOUR
ALL THE HUMANS.
[CHITTERING]
>> THESE FILTHY RATS HAVE
OVERRUN THE WHOLE REGION.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND YOU SAY WE HAVE NO WAY TO
BATTLE THE SWARMING HORDES
DIRECTLY?
>> NO, THEY DON'T DIE, EVEN IF
YOU SLAY THEM, SO THEY KEEP
INCREASING.
AND SINCE THEY'VE SPREAD SO FAR,
WE CAN'T TRACE THE SOURCE.
>> BY SOURCE YOU MEAN THE
MINIATURE SHRINE?
>> YES.
I HEARD THAT IF YOU DESTROY THE
SHRINE, THE RATS WILL DISAPPEAR.
>> THEY SEEM TO BE HEADED FOR
ONE PLACE.
>> THIS CAN ONLY MEAN ONE THING.
SOMEONE SOMEWHERE HAS CAST A
MAYOSE.
>> MAYOSE?
>> IT'S A SPELL THAT LURES
DEMONS TOGETHER AND DESTROYS
THEM.
BUT ONLY ONE WITH IMMENSE
SPIRITUAL POWER CAN CAST SUCH A
SPELL.
>> [THINKING] THE ONLY ONE
CAPABLE OF THIS IS KIKYO.
SO, THEN KIKYO IS AT THE END OF
THIS FLOW OF RATS.
>> OK, INUYASHA, LET'S GET
GOING.
>> HUH? KAGOME?
>> I'M GOING TO TRY TO FIND THE
SOURCE OF WHERE THE RATS ARE
COMING FROM.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> SOMEONE HAS TO.
THE RATS JUST KEEP ON COMING AND
THERE'S NO END IN SIGHT.
WHICH MEANS THAT THE SHRINE IS
STILL RELEASING RATS.
>> SO, WE MUST STOP THE SOURCE
OR IT WILL NOT END.
LET'S SPLIT INTO TWO GROUPS.
I'LL GO ALONG WITH SANGO.
>> INUYASHA, LOOK AT THAT.
THE RATS ARE CLIMBING THAT TREE.
>> THAT TREE'S REALLY TALL,
ISN'T IT?
>> YEAH, IT IS.
IT REACHES ALL THE WAY UP INTO
THE CLOUDS.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE THE RATS ARE
DISAPPEARING.
IS THIS THE MAYOSE?
>> [THINKING] WHY LET MORE
LOOSE?
KIKYO HAS ALREADY COME OUT OF
HIDING.
>> AND DON'T CLOSE THE DOORS.
>> [THINKING] DAMN HIM.
HE'S DOING THIS FOR HIS OWN
ENJOYMENT.
IF I CLOSE THESE DOORS, THE RATS
WILL STOP.
EVEN NOW, IT MAY SAVE SOME
LIVES.
HUH?
ARGH.
I'M BEING WATCHED.
IF I CLOSE THE DOORS, NARAKU
WILL KNOW THAT MY MEMORY HAS
RETURNED.
>> KOHAKU!
>> HUH?
>> DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE BEHIND
THIS.
>> [THINKING] SISTER.
>> KOHAKU.
ON MY WAY HERE, I SAW SO MANY
VILLAGES DEVOURED BY RATS.
HOW I WISH THAT YOU WERE NOT A
PART OF THIS.
>> UHH...
[THINKING] I CAN'T DISOBEY MY
ORDERS.
>> KOHAKU!
>> SANGO!
>> SANGO, DON'T DO IT!
YOU'LL JUST CREATE MORE RATS!
>> JUST TAKE CARE OF THE REST,
MIROKU.
>> SANGO, WAIT!
>> [PANTING]
[THINKING] I HAVE TO DESTROY
THAT SHRINE NO MATTER WHAT.
>> [GRUNT]
THEY DON'T EVEN NOTICE ME.
THEY'RE SO INTENT ON WHERE
THEY'RE GOING...
[THINKING] WHICH MEANS THE POWER
OF THE MAYOSE IS ENORMOUS.
>> [CHITTERING]
>> [THINKING] AMAZING.
>> WHAT HAPPENS TO THE RATS WHO
CLIMB UP THE TREE TO THE SKY?
>> I SUPPOSE THEY BECOME
PURIFIED.
>> [SIGH]
>> [THINKING] NO SIGN OF KIKYO.
>> SO SHE SET THE TRAP AND THEN
RAN AWAY.
BOTHERSOME WOMAN.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> UGH!
>> [GRUNT]
>> WHAT?
>> THEY LOOK LIKE DEMON SLUGS.
>> HUH?
>> THAT KIKYO--JUST WHEN I
THOUGHT I'D FINALLY LURED HER
OUT.
>> HAKUDOUSHI.
>> SHE LEAVES THIS SILLY TREE
AND GOES BACK INTO HIDING.
>> ARE YOU THE ONE WHO RELEASED
THE RATS?
>> HA HA.
DO YOU REALLY HAVE TO ASK?
>> THE SLUGS ARE DESTROYING THE
MAYOSE TREE.
IF THEY KEEP GOING, THE TREE
WILL FALL DOWN.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> GO AHEAD, DO YOUR WORST,
INUYASHA.
>> OH, I'LL SHOW YOU MY WORST.
>> INUYASHA, WAIT!
>> YOU CAN'T USE THE WIND-SCAR!
YOU'LL BREAK DOWN THE TREE,
AND THAT'S JUST WHAT HAKUDOUSHI
WANTS!
>> I KNEW THAT, SO QUIT WASTING
MY TIME!
[GRUNT]
>> OH, SURE HE KNEW THAT.
>> EITHER WAY, WE HAVE TO
PROTECT THE TREE.
IF THE WIND-SCAR WON'T WORK,
LET'S FIND OUT IF MY ARROW WILL.
>> [GRUNT]
>> ALL RIGHT!
THAT WAS GREAT, KAGOME.
>> WELL, I HAD A LARGE TARGET.
>> DON'T MOVE, YOU BASTARD.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW MANY
VILLAGES WERE DEVOURED BY YOUR
DEMON RATS JUST TO BRING KIKYO
OUT OF HIDING?
>> COME NOW.
IS THAT REALLY WHAT'S UPSETTING
YOU?
WHY MUST YOU PERSIST IN
INTERFERING WITH THINGS THAT
AREN'T YOUR CONCERN?
PERHAPS I'LL MEDDLE WITH THOSE
VILLAGERS WHO ARE TRYING TO RUN
AWAY.
>> WHY, YOU--
WIND-SCAR!
>> HE GOT HIM!
>> DID IT WORK?
>> [GRUNT]
>> [LAUGHING]
IF YOU SEE KIKYO, GIVE HER A
MESSAGE.
AS LONG AS SHE KEEPS RUNNING
FROM NARAKU, THE SAME THING WILL
HAPPEN OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
>> DAMN YOU.
HUH?
>> HUH? OHH!
>> [CHITTERING]
>> KAGOME, THE RATS ARE ACTING
DIFFERENT ALL OF A SUDDEN.
>> HUH?
>> UNTIL NOW THEY WERE ONLY
CONCERNED WITH GETTING TO THE
TREE.
>> THIS ISN'T GOOD.
MAYBE THE SPIRITUAL POWER OF THE
TREE IS WEAKENING.
>> OH, NO.
>> WE'VE GOT TO HURRY AND GET
RID OF THE DEMON SLUGS.
INUYASHA!
TAKE CARE OF THE DEMONS HIGHER
UP THE TREE.
>> I'M ON IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
I HOPE THEY DON'T GET HUNGRY.
>> [PANTING]
>> HUH?
>> KOHAKU!
>> [GRUNT]
>> PLEASE LISTEN TO ME.
YOU REALLY DON'T HAVE TO DO
THIS, KOHAKU.
>> [THINKING] SISTER.
>> HMM?
>> [CHITTERING]
>> OH, NO.
THE RATS ARE ALL COMING BACK.
[THINKING] THE ZUSHI NEZUMI ARE
TRYING TO GET BACK TO THE
SHRINE.
DOES THIS MEAN THE SPELL'S
BROKEN?
UGH! WIND TUNNEL!
HUH?
UGH!
[THINKING] THIS IS BAD.
I CAN'T GET THEM ALL.
THERE ARE JUST TOO MANY.
>> KOHAKU!
GIVE ME THE SHRINE.
IF THAT SHRINE IS DESTROYED,
THE RATS WILL DISAPPEAR.
YOU ARE A DEMON SLAYER, KOHAKU.
PLEASE REMEMBER THAT.
>> [THINKING] THE SAIMYOUSHOU
ARE WATCHING.
IF I DO ANYTHING THAT SEEMS LIKE
A BETRAYAL TO NARAKU, I'LL NEVER
BE ABLE TO GET NEAR NARAKU'S
HEART.
HUH?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [THINKING] THE RATS.
>> THIS IS THE LAST ONE!
>> WE'VE DESTROYED ALL THE
SLUGS.
>> UH-OH.
HOW COME THE RATS AREN'T TRYING
TO CLIMB UP THE TREE, KAGOME?
>> I SUPPOSE THE TREE MUST'VE
DIED.
>> OH, NO, I THINK THEY'RE
HUNGRY AGAIN.
>> DAMN YOU!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
I THINK I'M JUST MAKING THINGS
WORSE.
THESE RATS ARE REALLY STARTING
TO ANNOY ME.
SHIPPO, SNAP OUT OF IT AND
TRANSFORM.
WE'RE GETTING OUT OF HERE.
>> WE'RE RUNNING AWAY?
>> THE MAYOSE TREE ISN'T ANY
GOOD TO US NOW.
I'M GOING TO DESTROY THAT
SHRINE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TRANSFORM!
>> OH, NO.
THE RATS HAVE BROKEN OUT OF
FORMATION AND ARE SCATTERING.
>> HEY, CAN'T YOU FLY ANY
FASTER?
>> NOT WITH YOU WEIGHING ME
DOWN.
>> SANGO!
>> MIROKU!
>> DESTROY THE SHRINE!
HURRY!
>> CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND, KOHAKU?
IF YOU DON'T DO SOMETHING SOON,
THE RATS WILL DESTROY YOU, TOO!
>> [THINKING] THIS IS WHAT
NARAKU WOULD EXPECT ME TO DO--
PROTECT THE SHRINE, EVEN IF IT
MEANT MY DEATH.
SO I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO FIGHT
SANGO.
>> KOHAKU, YOU HAVE TO WAKE UP.
>> [THINKING] SISTER!
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> BE CAREFUL!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> KOHAKU?
>> SANGO, GET ON KIRARA.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS DOWN HERE.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [PANTING]
AAH!
>> KOHAKU!
>> [GROANING]
>> DAMN THING.
I'LL SMASH THIS CURSED SHRINE!
>> HUH? IT WON'T BREAK.
>> IS IT BEING PROTECTED BY A
DEMONIC BARRIER?
HURRY AND GET AWAY, SANGO.
>> KOHAKU.
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA!
>> I'M GOING ON AHEAD.
[THINKING] THE SMELL OF BLOOD.
DAMN IT!
I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING ABOUT
THIS.
I THINK SANGO IS IN REAL
TROUBLE.
>> [THINKING] IS THAT A SACRED
JEWEL SHARD?
KOHAKU.
PLEASE HURRY UP, SHIPPO.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M TRYING.
>> UGH! SANGO!
UHH!
CURSE THESE RATS!
IF I USE MY WIND TUNNEL, IT'LL
TAKE SANGO AS WELL.
>> MIROKU, WHERE'S SANGO?
>> SHE'S UNDER THERE.
>> AGH!
A SACRED ARROW?
>> I THINK THE DEMONIC BARRIER
IS GONE.
TRY TO BREAK THE SHRINE.
HURRY!
>> AAH!
[GRUNTING]
>> THEY'RE GONE.
>> KAGOME, THE RATS ARE
DISAPPEARING.
>> THE SHRINE MUST'VE BEEN
BROKEN.
>> KIKYO.
>> [PANTING]
[GRUNT]
>> UHH...
>> SANGO?
>> [THINKING] SISTER.
SHE'S BADLY HURT.
ALL BECAUSE OF ME.
SISTER...
SISTER.
SISTER!
[GROAN]
>> [GROAN]
KOHAKU?
KOHAKU, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> [THINKING] SISTER.
>> KOHAKU?
WAIT!
>> LOOK, SAIMYOUSHOU.
>> TELL ME, WHO IS THAT WOMAN,
KOHAKU?
WHY DID SHE PROTECT YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
[THINKING] HAKUDOUSHI.
SO YOU WERE WATCHING ME.
SISTER, I DON'T WANT TO PUT YOU
IN HARM'S WAY ANYMORE.
I MUST DESTROY NARAKU AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE.
>> KOHAKU!
KOHAKU?
>> SANGO.
>> POOR GIRL.
>> I WONDER IF SANGO'S GOING TO
BE OK.
SHE WAS BADLY BITTEN BY THE
DEMON RATS.
>> [GRUNT]
PHYSICALLY, SHE'LL PROBABLY BE
OK.
I GOTTA HAND IT TO HER.
SHE IS PRETTY STRONG FOR A
HUMAN.
>> BUT PSYCHOLOGICALLY, SHE WAS
QUITE TRAUMATIZED TO LEARN THAT
KOHAKU WAS INVOLVED IN USING THE
SHRINE.
>> SANGO, ARE YOU IN ANY PAIN?
>> I CANNOT FORGIVE KOHAKU FOR
WHAT HE DID.
>> SANGO...
>> BECAUSE OF THOSE RATS, MANY
VILLAGES WERE DESTROYED.
NOT ONLY THAT...
>> [SCREAMING]
>> AAH!
>> [THINKING] NO, I DON'T WANT
TO.
>> [GROANING]
>> [THINKING] I DON'T WANT TO
KILL THEM.
>> KOHAKU!
AT THE CASTLE THAT WAS ASSAULTED
BY THE BIRDS, HE KILLED MANY
PEOPLE.
THESE PEOPLE WEREN'T KILLED BY
THE BIRDS.
EVEN IF NARAKU ORDERED IT, WHAT
KOHAKU DID IS UNFORGIVABLE.
I KNOW THAT IN MY HEAD, BUT WHEN
KOHAKU WAS ATTACKED BY THE RATS,
I FELT AS THOUGH MY HEART WAS
BEING CRUSHED.
THEN WHEN I SAW THAT HE WAS OK,
I FELT RELIEF FROM THE BOTTOM OF
MY HEART.
THOUGH I SHOULD, I CAN'T HATE
KOHAKU.
>> SANGO, IT'S OK.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE TO HATE HIM.
>> YES, BUT AFTER ALL OF THIS--
>> ANSWER TRUTHFULLY, SANGO.
DO YOU REGRET PROTECTING KOHAKU?
>> YES, I DO.
BUT IF I HADN'T PROTECTED HIM, I
THINK--I THINK I WOULD REGRET IT
MORE.
>> AND THAT'S FINE.
THAT IS SIMPLY THE WAY OF THE
HUMAN HEART.
>> YES.
[THINKING] THANK YOU, MIROKU.
>> [THINKING] NARAKU, YOU WOULD
STOOP TO SUCH DEPTHS JUST TO
LURE ME OUT?
ASUKA, KOCHO.
TAKE THIS AND GO.
[THINKING] IF NARAKU WANTS ME, I
WILL GO FIND HIM.
>> [MUSIC]
>> AFTER A LONG ABSENCE, I
RETURN TO THE PRESENT AND FACE
COUNTLESS QUESTIONS ABOUT
INUYASHA.
>> IS YOUR BOYFRIEND REALLY AT
YOUR HOUSE?
>> AW, COME ON, I WANT TO MEET
HIM.
>> HE'S A REAL TROUBLEMAKER,
ISN'T HE?
>> HEY, INUYASHA BROKE THAT BIKE
THAT MOM GAVE TO SIS.
>> LEAVE IT TO ME.
I'LL PAY YOU BACK.
>> WHAT?
YOU'RE GOING TO USE THE ADAMANT
BARRAGE TO CREATE DIAMONDS?
NEXT TIME, "THE LUCKY BUT
TWO-TIMING SCOUNDREL!"
>> I'LL MAKE A TON OF THEM WITH
THE TETSUSAIGA.