- HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
- A STRONG DEMONIC AURA.
[ROARS]
- HUH?
- BE CAREFUL.
THE EVIL IS DRAWING NEAR.
- WHERE ARE YOU?
COME ON AND SHOW YOURSELF.
[GRASS RUSTLING]
- IT'S UNDERGROUND.
- AAH!
[SHRIEKING]
- UNH!
- YUCK! WHAT IS THAT JUNK?
IT'S MELTING THE GROUND!
- SHIPPO!
- WHOA!
- I'LL STOP IT!
- TAKE THIS!
[SHOUTING]
- YAAH!
- AAH!
[ROARS]
- IT'S OVER!
- HANG ON!
- HUH? WHAT NOW?
- [GRUNTING]
- UNH!
- IT CAN'T FIGHT ANYMORE.
- THANKS FOR NOTHING!
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO
SLICE AND DICE THAT THING!
- WELL, IT'S NO LOSS.
IT HARDLY PUT UP A FIGHT.
- [SIGHS]
IT'S DISAPPOINTING
WHEN A DEMON'S APPEARANCE
IS SO DECEIVING.
- ALL'S WELL THAT ENDS WELL,
AND THAT'S WHAT COUNTS.
- [PEOPLE CHEERING]
- WHAT'S UP WITH THOSE GUYS?
- HMM.
OH, WE ARE FOREVER INDEBTED,
ITINERANT MONK.
YOU SEE, THAT DEMON HAS BEEN
RELENTLESSLY TORMENTING
OUR VILLAGE.
- THAT DEMON HAS?
- SHH.
- HMM?
- OH, PLEASE LET US
REPAY YOUR KINDNESS
WITH A SMALL BANQUET
IN YOUR HONOR.
- [CLAMORING]
- I WAS MERELY CARRYING
OUT MY DUTY.
I MUST DECLINE, SIR.
- HOW DISAPPOINTING.
WHAT A SHAME.
HOW WILL I EXPLAIN THIS TO
THE BEAUTIFUL YOUNG GIRLS
OF THE VILLAGE,
WHO EAGERLY AWAIT YOU?
- HUH?
- OH, WELL.
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
THEN AGAIN, I WOULDN'T
WANT TO BE PUNISHED
BY THE GODS FOR
REJECTING YOUR KINDNESS.
- HUH?
- FUNNY HOW THE MENTION
OF YOUNG GIRLS
CAN CHANGE HIS MIND.
- HE'S SUCH A LECHEROUS MONK.
- [LAUGHING]
- "FAREWELL DAYS OF MY YOUTH."
- THESE BEANS ARE DELICIOUS.
- IT'S SO YUMMY!
THEY'RE GREAT!
IT'S BEEN A WHILE SINCE
WE'VE HAD SUCH GREAT FOOD.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, SANGO?
YOU HAVEN'T TOUCHED YOUR FOOD.
- YOUR PALM SAYS THAT YOU WILL
BE BLESSED WITH MANY OFFSPRING.
- [GASPS]
- MY DEAR,
WOULD YOU CONSIDER
BEARING MY CHILDREN?
- OH, YES!
- GAAH!
- I'LL HAVE AS MANY AS YOU WANT.
15 OR 16--
YOU CHOOSE THE NUMBER.
LET'S GET TO IT.
- AAH!
HELP, SANGO!
DON'T JUST SIT THERE AND WATCH!
DO SOMETHING!
- HMM.
YOU'VE FINALLY FOUND
SOMEONE WILLING AND ABLE.
YOU HAVE MY BLESSINGS.
- NOW, THAT'S A COLD SHOULDER.
- RIGHT THIS WAY.
- AFTER THE YOUNG MEN AGAIN,
ARE YOU, GRANNY?
- OH, I MAY BE OLD,
BUT I AIN'T RUSTY.
HA HA HA HA!
- [LAUGHING]
- I DIDN'T KNOW THEY HAD
FAMILY REUNIONS IN THIS ERA.
MAKES ME ALL WARM AND FUZZY.
- WHAT'S A FAMILY UNION?
- HMM?
MMM...
IT'S WHEN PARENTS
AND GRANDPARENTS AND SIBLINGS
ALL GET TOGETHER TO EAT
AND ENJOY EACH OTHER'S COMPANY.
- HMM?
ARRGH!
THANKS, BUT NO, THANKS.
[GROANING]
AAH!
- DON'T BE SO RUDE.
BESIDES, YOU SHOULDN'T LIE
DOWN RIGHT AFTER A MEAL.
- YEAH? SAYS WHO?
- [SMOOCHING SOUND]
- MMH!
- HMM?
- MYOGA?!
- OHH.
I WAS A BIT CONCERNED
ABOUT YOU,
MASTER INUYASHA,
SO I SOUGHT YOU OUT...
ONLY TO FIND YOU BATTLING
A FEROCIOUS CENTIPEDE.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE SAFE.
- FUNNY HOW YOU'RE
NOWHERE TO BE FOUND
WHEN WE'RE IN BATTLE,
YET YOU NEVER MISS A BEAT
WHEN THERE'S FOOD
AND WOMEN AROUND,
YOU LITTLE SCHEMER.
- NOW, NOW, LET'S NOT BE CRUEL.
- WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN ALL
THIS TIME, ANYWAY, MYOGA?
- [CHUCKLES]
EVEN OLD PESTS LIKE ME
HAVE SOME BEDFELLOWS THEY'D
PREFER TO KEEP SECRET, YOU KNOW.
[LAUGHING]
- ARRGH.
DEFINITELY A CREEPY CRAWLER.
UNH!
- OOH, OOH, AH, AH, AH!
HOT, HOT!
HOTTER THAN HOT!
OOH, OOH!
[WOLF HOWLING]
- [SNORES]
OHH...
I COULDN'T EAT ANOTHER BITE.
AH...
AHH.
[SNORING]
[BOING BOING]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
SILENTLY, STEALTHILY,
HE SNEAKS THROUGH THE NIGHT.
HA HA.
- [FOOTSTEPS]
- A GHOST.
I'VE HEARD OF SPIRITS
OF CHILDREN
THAT LINGER ON IN OLD MANSIONS
AFTER THEIR PASSING.
THIS MUST BE ONE SUCH PHANTOM.
HMM.
YAAAAH!
ARRGH!
MMH!
WHO ARE YOU?
- MMM.
WEE WEE.
- NO! NOT HERE!
- GOT TO GO.
- JUST WAIT!
THIS ISN'T THE TOILET!
THAT'S A BOY.
[TINKLING]
- [SIGHS]
IF I'M GOING TO BE
AWAKE AT THIS HOUR,
I CAN THINK OF OTHER THINGS
I'D RATHER BE DOING.
- [GROANS]
[OWL HOOTING]
- [FOOTSTEPS]
- MMM.
YOU HAVE TO PEE AGAIN,
I SUPPOSE.
BE A GOOD BOY AND GO
BY YOURSELF THIS TIME, OK?
[GROANS]
HUH?
SANGO.
UH, UH...
DO YOU KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS?
WHAT LUCK!
SHE'S FINALLY COME
SNEAKING INTO MY BED.
LIE DOWN.
COME JOIN ME.
HUH?
AAH!
UNH!
AW, COME ON!
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE STILL
ANGRY ABOUT EARLIER!
AAH, UNH!
UHH...
AAH! AAH!
THE OLD WOMAN WAS JUST JOKING!
AAH!
[CRASH]
- OH, MAN, WHAT'S ALL THIS
RUCKUS ABOUT OUT HERE?
HUH?
- SANGO, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE SO ANGRY!
COME ON, I'M TELLING
THE TRUTH!
AIEE!
UNH! YAAH!
UH, UH!
[WHIMPERING]
- [BREATHING SHALLOWLY]
- UHH...
SHE'S ATTACKING ME IN HER SLEEP.
- [YAWNS]
CAN'T YOU TWO KEEP YOUR LITTLE
SQUABBLES A BIT QUIETER?
- WAIT!
- HUH?
- [GROANS]
- SANGO IS POSSESSED
BY SOMETHING!
- SANGO, WAKE UP!
- UNH!
- AAH!
- STOP IT, SANGO!
- UHH!
- UNH.
- SANGO!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HUH?
AAH!
MMH!
- ARRGH...
HMM?
- UH...
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU, MIROKU?
- WOW.
SHE EVEN SLAPS HIM IN HER SLEEP.
- SOMEONE BEWITCHED SANGO
RIGHT UNDER OUR NOSES.
- UH, I DON'T REMEMBER A THING.
- THAT'S STRANGE.
WHO WOULD DO THAT
TO HER, THOUGH?
- I DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA,
BUT I DON'T SENSE ANY
EVIL AROUND THIS PLACE.
- ARE YOU CERTAIN?
- HUH?
MYOGA, WHEN DID YOU
JUMP ON MIROKU?
- ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T
SENSE ANYTHING SUSPICIOUS?
- ARE YOU HIDING
SOMETHING FROM US?
- I, UH, NOT ESPECIALLY, NO.
- HMM. WAIT A MINUTE.
A LONG TIME AGO,
MY FATHER TOLD ME ABOUT DEMONS
WHO ONLY REALIZE THEIR
TRUE POWER AFTER DEATH.
- THEY'RE POWERFUL AFTER DEATH?
- THE MOST RECENT DEMON
WE DESTROYED WAS...
- [GASPS]
- HUH?
YOU MEAN, THAT GIANT CENTIPEDE
THAT WAS SO WEAK IS WHAT
POSSESSED SANGO?
- YOU'D BETTER SEAL ITS
POWERS UP ONE MORE TIME,
JUST IN CASE.
- [WHIMPERING]
- [GRUNTING]
- HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU, MYOGA?
- NOTHING.
NOTHING AT ALL!
- [GRUNTING]
- IT'S JUST A CARCASS.
- WELL, NOTHING
SUSPICIOUS ABOUT IT.
- I THINK I'D BETTER
SEAL IT WITH ANOTHER SUTRA,
JUST TO BE ON THE SAFE SIDE.
- OOH.
KAGOME, YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY LUCK WITH MEN.
- OH, I DON'T?
- YOU WON'T FIND
PEACE OR HAPPINESS
UNLESS YOU LEAVE
YOUR CURRENT MAN.
- HUH?
- WHAT ABOUT YOU, SANGO?
LET'S SEE.
HMM.
YOUR LUCK WITH MEN IS NO BETTER.
YOU'D BEST FORGET ABOUT HIM.
HE'S TOO MUCH OF A WOMANIZER.
- YOUR PALM READING IS RIGHT
ON THE MARK, MYOGA.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- HUH?
WHAT?
ARE YOU GUYS BURYING
THE DEMON ALREADY?
[GROWLING]
- NO, WE'RE NOT FINISHED YET.
GET UP HERE AND HELP, MIROKU!
- HRRM.
- HUH?
- I WON'T FORGIVE YOU FOR THIS!
- AAH!
- WHAT?
- UNH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING--
IS THIS SOME SORT OF PAYBACK?!
- YOU HAVE FINALLY
REVEALED YOUR TRUE SELF,
YOU LECHEROUS MONK!
- UNH! AAH!
I DIDN'T REALLY THINK YOU WERE
THAT TYPE OF MAN, MIROKU.
I WAS WRONG ABOUT YOU.
- AND I WAS RIGHT ALL ALONG.
- I THINK YOU'RE BOTH WRONG.
THE SPIRIT OF THE CENTIPEDE
MUST HAVE POSSESSED
MIROKU THIS TIME.
- THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
IT WOULD TAKE A LOT OF
POWER TO POSSESS MIROKU,
AND I DON'T SENSE THAT.
- UNH!
AAH!
[GROWLS]
- AAH!
- HIDE, SHIPPO!
YOU MUST RUN TO SAFETY!
- I FIGURED THAT MUCH OUT.
WHOA!
- UNH!
YOU WON'T ESCAPE, YOU WRETCH!
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- ARRGH!
UNH!
UHH.
THIS BODY IS INADEQUATE,
IF EVEN THAT YOUNG CHILD
CAN OUTRUN ME.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR VOICE?
WHY ARE YOU TALKING LIKE THAT?
- SEE? I TOLD YOU
HE WAS POSSESSED.
- WHY, YOU...
[BOING BOING]
- UNH...UMM.
- HMM?
- UNH, UNH.
WHAT ON EARTH HAPPENED TO ME?
- OH!
HEY, MIROKU,
HAVE YOU RETURNED
TO THE OLD YOU AGAIN?
- OH!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- THERE'S YOUR ANSWER!
HE HAS DEFINITELY RETURNED
TO HIS OLD SELF, INUYASHA!
- YEP, THAT'S FOR SURE.
HMM? HANG ON.
THERE'S SOMETHING EVIL
COMING THIS WAY.
- HUH?
[RUMBLING]
- AAH!
- [DEMON ROARING]
- WHAT IS THAT?
- DO YOU THINK IT COULD BE
THE OTHER CENTIPEDE'S MATE?
- MAYBE THIS IS THE ONE
THAT POSSESSED US.
- [DEMON ROARING]
- AAH!
- BE CAREFUL!
THAT STUFF'S ACID!
- STAY HERE.
ARRGH!
TAKE THIS!
WIND SCAR!
- [DEMON SHRIEKING]
- HUH.
UNH.
- AH!
- THAT'S THE END OF ANOTHER
TROUBLESOME CENTIPEDE.
- LOOKS LIKE I'D BETTER
SEAL UP ITS POWERS.
[BOING BOING BOING]
THIS PUTS AN END TO THIS AFFAIR.
- [SIGHS]
HRRM...
- [LAUGHING]
- WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
- INUYASHA?
- HMM?
- ARRGH.
- AAH!
- HUH?
- COME BACK HERE!
YOU'LL NEVER ESCAPE ME!
- DON'T TELL ME HE'S
POSSESSED NOW.
- WATCH HOW HE'S RUNNING.
HE KIND OF LOOKS LIKE A FLEA.
- LIKE A FLEA?
- I'LL GET YOU!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOW INUYASHA'S GONE CRAZY.
- I'M COMING, MYOGA!
- INUYASHA'S CALLING YOU.
- THAT'S NOT MASTER INUYASHA.
- WHAT?
- YOU'LL NEVER GET AWAY FROM ME!
- [GRUNTING]
- UHH...WHOA!
WHOA!
UHH!
IS THAT YOU, INUYASHA?
- [SIGHS]
DON'T THINK THAT YOU
CAN ESCAPE FROM ME,
YOU NAUGHTY LITTLE RASCAL.
I'M ALL YOURS FOR THE TAKING,
MY SWEET FOXY DARLING.
- INUYASHA, SNAP OUT OF IT!
- WE'RE MEANT FOR EACH OTHER.
- [SIGHS]
- EEEK!
OOH!
WHAT ABOUT MY DREAMS OF
FALLING IN LOVE WITH A WOMAN,
NOT A POSSESSED
MALE HALF-DEMON?
OOH!
- [PANTING]
- INUYASHA, SIT, BOY!
- UNH!
- OHH!
- ARRGH!
WHAT DID YOU DO
THAT FOR, KAGOME?
- THANK GOODNESS.
YOU'RE BACK TO NORMAL AGAIN.
- [GRUNTING]
- DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
- WOULD YOU GET OFF ME,
YOU RABID DOG?!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
- INUYASHA, WHAT DO YOU
HAVE THERE IN YOUR HAND?
- HMM?
OH.
HMM.
- PLEASE RELEASE ME!
- IT'S MYOGA!
- LET ME GO, MASTER INUYASHA,
I BEG YOU!
- UNH!
KAGOME, IT'S A FLEA--
AN UNFAMILIAR FLEA!
- HE'S RIGHT.
- IT CAME OUT FROM
INUYASHA'S BODY.
- I'LL NEVER ASK ANOTHER FAVOR.
JUST LET ME GO!
- MYOGA, THIS IS THE END
OF THE LINE FOR YOU.
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU CANNOT
GET AWAY THIS TIME.
- HUH?
UH, EXCUSE ME.
WHO ARE YOU?
- [GROANING]
- [LAUGHING]
OH, DEAR.
HOW RUDE OF ME.
MY NAME IS SHOGA,
AND ACCORDING TO OUR
PARENTS' WISHES,
MYOGA AND I ARE
BETROTHED TO BE WED.
- NOT TRUE, NOT TRUE!
- YOU BE QUIET!
- YES'M.
- HMM?
- OLD LADY SHOGA?
- DON'T CALL HER OLD.
- NO INSULT TAKEN.
WHEN A FLEA REACHES MY AGE,
SHE WANTS TO SETTLE DOWN
AND HAVE A FAMILY,
BUT YOU KNOW MY MYOGA HERE.
[CRYING]
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN
SUCH A WOMANIZER.
WHENEVER THERE'S
A HANDSOME WOMAN AROUND,
HE STEALS OUT TO FLIRT WITH HER
WITHOUT A WORD OF
APOLOGY TO ME...
AND LEAVES NARY A CLUE
TO TRACK HIM DOWN,
AND I'M LEFT HELPLESS
TO AWAIT HIS RETURN.
THIS TIME I HUNTED HIM DOWN,
SWEARING TO LUG HIM BACK HOME
EVEN IF I NEEDED TO USE
A LITTLE FORCE.
- [YELLING]
- SCARY.
- THE DREAM IS OVER!
- MYOGA, ARE YOU PREPARED?
- NO. HELP!
RELEASE ME, MASTER INUYASHA!
- NO CAN DO.
- WHY? TELL ME WHY!
- YOU KNEW THAT
OLD LADY SHOGA WAS THE ONE
WHO BEWITCHED US
ALL ALONG, MYOGA.
- OH!
HRRM!
- PLEASE!
SURELY YOU WOULDN'T
ROB AN INNOCENT FELLOW
OF HIS PRECIOUS YOUTH.
- PRECIOUS YOUTH, MY FEET!
I'LL STRAP YOU TO MY BACK
IF THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES
TO GET YOU HOME!
- GOOD PLAN.
- NOW, NOW, OLD LADY SHOGA,
I THINK YOU SHOULD
FORGIVE HIM, HMM?
- YEAH. HE'S RIGHT.
INSTEAD OF TAKING MYOGA'S
FREEDOM AWAY FROM HIM,
WHY NOT STAY HERE
AND GET MARRIED?
- UH-UH-UHH!
GET MARRIED?!
[CRYING]
- AND THEN YOU CAN
START A HOME TOGETHER.
- [SOBBING]
- SHE'S EMBARRASSED.
- A FEMALE'S STILL A FEMALE,
EVEN IF SHE'S A FLEA.
- WE CAN EVEN ASK
THE HEADMAN OF THE VILLAGE
TO BE THE GO-BETWEEN.
- THERE'S NO NEED
FOR THE HEADMAN!
PLEASE, PLEASE!
- MYOGA DOESN'T SEEM
PLEASED ABOUT THIS.
- HE'LL JUST HAVE
TO RESIGN HIMSELF.
- YOU WILL MAKE A FINE
COUPLE OF FLEAS.
- KILL WE NOW.
- [WEEPING]
- [APPLAUSE]
- MYOGA, AT LAST WE
ARE FLEA AND WIFE.
DON'T BE SO SHY, DEAREST.
[GIGGLING]
YOU COULD AT LEAST
SAY YOU LOVE ME.
HUH?
MYOGA?
HMM?
AAAH!
- HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- SHOGA?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- THIS ISN'T MYOGA.
HE SWITCHED PLACES
WITH SOME STRANGE FLEA.
- AAH!
- THAT MYOGA--HE RAN AWAY!
- RUN, RUN!
RUN TO THE END
OF THE EARTH, PLEASE!
- [YOWLS]
- WHY, THAT OLD GEEZER!
GET BACK HERE!
- HUH?
- [BOING BOING]
YOU WON'T GET AWAY WITH THIS!
- [MEOWING]
- RUN!
RUN FOR MY LIFE!
- COME BACK HERE!
- WHEN IT COMES TO FLEEING,
MYOGA IS DEFINITELY THE BEST.
- [ALL SIGH]
- STOP, MYOGA!
- NO WAY!
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- INUYASHA, CAN'T YOU FIND
NARAKU'S CASTLE YET?
- STOP YAKKING.
I CAN'T CONCENTRATE.
- TONIGHT'S THE NEW MOON.
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR
SENSE OF SMELL?
- YOU WISH.
I KNOW THIS SCENT.
IT'S KOGA OF
THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE.
- THAT'S THE LEAST
OF OUR WORRIES.
KAGURA IS MAKING A DEAL
WITH SESSHOMARU.
- NEXT TIME, "NARAKU'S BARRIER,
KAGURA'S DECISION."
DAMN!
OF ALL THE TIMES!