- I GUESS EVEN A LARGE CASTLE
CAN BE DIFFICULT TO FIND.
- ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY DIRECTIONS
OR LANDMARKS TO GO BY.
- COME ON. YOU GOT TO BE
FULLY RECOVERED BY NOW.
YOU WANT TO HUNT DOWN THAT
NARAKU CREEP, TOO, RIGHT?
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST
JOIN US FOR A WHILE?
- HMM.
- WELL, YOU COULD SHOW SOME
ENTHUSIASM FOR MY OFFER.
WE KNOW A HECK OF A LOT MORE
ABOUT NARAKU THAN YOU DO.
PLUS, YOU'RE ALONE NOW.
YOU GOT NOTHING TO LOSE
FROM TAGGING ALONG WITH US.
- HMM.
- HE'S RIGHT.
LET'S TAKE IT
ONE STEP AT A TIME
AND FOCUS ON GATHERING
THE JEWEL SHARDS.
WE WON'T HAVE TO
CHASE NARAKU.
IF WE KEEP COLLECTING
THE SHARDS,
HE'LL EVENTUALLY COME TO US.
I KNOW YOU'RE HUNGRY
FOR REVENGE,
BUT YOU MUST BE PATIENT.
- I SEE.
- PLEASE BELIEVE ME.
I UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL.
- THANK YOU,
BUT IS IT NECESSARY TO
KEEP STROKING MY LEGS
WHILE YOU TALK?
- HEH HEH HEH.
- AT LEAST HE DIDN'T START
HITTING ON HER
UNTIL SHE WAS FEELING BETTER.
- MIROKU, TRY TO
CONTROL YOURSELF, WILL YOU?
- [GRUNTING]
- TELL US, WHAT WERE YOU
ABLE TO SEE, SHIPPO?
- THERE'S A LARGE LAKE JUST OVER
THAT HILL TO THE NORTH.
A HUGE SHRINE IS RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF IT.
- YOU SURE IT'S A SHRINE?
- IS IT NARAKU'S CASTLE?
- [PEOPLE GROANING
AND SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
- MUST HAVE BEEN A FLOOD.
- TERRIBLE.
[GONG RINGING]
- HMM?
- BEHOLD THE HUMAN SACRIFICE.
- WE WITHSTOOD
A DEVASTATING FLOOD THIS YEAR.
- I WONDER WHOSE CHILD IT IS.
- A CHILD SACRIFICE?
- THAT IS UTTERLY BARBARIC.
- PLEASE RECONSIDER,
HEADMAN.
- WHY DO YOU EVEN ASK?
IT IS ONLY NATURAL WE GIVE UP
OUR FIRST-BORN CHILDREN
TO PROTECT THE VILLAGE.
- WHAT'S SO NATURAL ABOUT THAT?
THIS SACRIFICE IS
FOR YOUR WATER GOD?
I BET HE'S JUST
SOME HYPED-UP DEMON.
- [GASP]
- A DEMON IS TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
HIS NEWFOUND STRENGTH
FROM A JEWEL SHARD.
DON'T EVEN TRY
HIDING ANYTHING FROM US.
- WH-WHO ARE YOU?
- NEVER SEEN THE LIKES BEFORE.
- LOOK AT HIS EARS!
ARE YOU A DEMON?
- LISTEN WELL.
THIS IS A PEACEFUL VILLAGE
PROTECTED BY A GREAT WATER GOD.
DEMONS ARE NOT WELCOME HERE.
- ARE YOU TALKING TO ME,
OLD MAN?
- STOP IT!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MIROKU?
- OUR COMPANY IS NOT HOSTILE.
OUR MISSION IS
TO TRAVEL AROUND THE COUNTRY
AND ASSIST THOSE
WHO ARE IN NEED OF HELP.
WE'VE HEARD OF
YOUR MISFORTUNE.
IF YOU ALLOW ME,
I WILL EXORCISE YOUR VILLAGE.
- ARE YOU REALLY THAT POWERFUL?
- I THINK AN EXORCISM
IS AN EXCELLENT IDEA.
- DO NOT BE
SO EASILY DECEIVED, MEN.
THEY ARE CONNIVING
IMPOSTORS.
- I BEG OF YOU, HEADMAN,
AT LEAST HEAR
WHAT THEY HAVE TO SAY.
- IF WE INDULGE THE WHIMS
OF SHYSTERS
AND RELY ON THEIR TRICKERY
ONLY TO RAISE THE IRE
OF THE WATER GOD,
WHO KNOWS WHAT ELSE
MIGHT BEFALL OUR VILLAGE?
HOW CAN I JUSTIFY
AN EXORCISM NOW
WHEN IT'S MY SON'S TURN
TO BE SACRIFICED?
HOW CAN I RISK UNDOING
ALL THE SACRIFICES
MADE BY THE CHILDREN
WHO WENT BEFORE HIM?
- [GASP]
- IS THAT THE CHILD
TO BE SACRIFICED?
- WE MUST DELIVER THE SACRIFICE
BEFORE THE SUN SETS.
HURRY UP.
CONTINUE THE PROCESSION.
- [MEN GROANING]
- THE GUY WITH THE MUSTACHE
IS WEIRD.
I DON'T TRUST HIM.
- I AGREE.
HE'S ACTING AS THOUGH HE WANTS
HIS SON TO BE SACRIFICED.
- HE WAS STRANGELY UPSET
WITH OUR INTERFERENCE.
- WELL, I GUESS WE MOVE ON
AND LET THEM DUNK THE KID.
- NOT ON YOUR LIFE.
WE ARE GONNA GO SAVE
THAT LITTLE BOY, RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- HUH?
- THEN FOLLOW ME.
HEY, YOU WANT TO BE
LEFT BEHIND?
- WHAT'S WITH HIM?
BOSSY KID.
- YOU CAN HAVE 'EM.
TAKE YOUR PICK.
- WHAT IS THIS GARBAGE?
- OOH, THERE ARE
SOME VALUABLE ARTICLES HERE.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
SUCH FINE SILK BEFORE.
- YOU DONE CHOOSING?
GOOD. THEN CONSIDER
YOURSELF HIRED.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, HIRED?
- I HEARD YOU BRAGGING
TO THE VILLAGERS
COMING TO PEOPLE'S AID
IS YOUR MISSION,
SO I WANT YOU TO LIVE UP TO
YOUR REPUTATION.
YOU'RE WORKING FOR ME NOW
TO DESTROY THE WATER GOD.
UNH!
WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?!
[GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA, STOP!
HE'S ONLY A LITTLE BOY!
- HE NEEDS TO BE TAUGHT
WHO THE BOSS IS AROUND HERE.
- JUST APOLOGIZE,
EVEN IF YOU DON'T MEAN IT.
INUYASHA CAN BE REALLY CHILDISH
SOMETIMES.
- THE HUMAN SACRIFICE IS TAKEN
TO THE SHRINE IN A BOAT,
SO WE'LL FOLLOW THE BOAT
AND ATTACK IT
WHEN THE WATER GOD SURFACES
AND IS ABOUT TO DEVOUR
THE SACRIFICE.
GOT THAT?
- THESE ARE STOLEN GOODS.
I JUST KNOW IT.
- THAT'S NONE OF OUR CONCERN.
- WELL, THEN,
WE SHOULDN'T TAKE THEM.
- ARE YOU PAYING ATTENTION?
- HMM.
SO, WHOSE CHILD ARE YOU,
ANYWAY?
- HMM?
MY FAMILY IS
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- YOU KNOW, I'VE GOT
A SNEAKING SUSPICION
YOU'RE THE REAL SON OF
THE HEADMAN, NOT THE OTHER BOY.
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
THEY'VE GOT THE SAME EYEBROWS
AND FOREHEAD.
- AND THE SAME ATTITUDE.
- SO THE BOY IN THE PROCESSION
WAS A STAND-IN?
- YES.
MY NAME IS TAROMARU,
AND I'M THE HEADMAN'S HEIR.
- I THOUGHT SO.
- WHY ARE YOU SO EAGER
TO DO THIS?
- THE WATER GOD STARTED
DEMANDING HUMAN SACRIFICES
FROM OUR VILLAGE
ABOUT HALF A YEAR AGO.
WE'VE HAD HEAVY RAINS
AND FLOODING.
THE WATER GOD SAID THAT
IN ORDER TO LIFT THE CURSE,
A HUMAN SACRIFICE
WAS NECESSARY.
A CHILD WAS SELECTED
WHEN A WHITE ARROW LANDED
ON THE ROOF OF HIS HOME.
FATHER WOULD ALWAYS SAY...
- PLEASE BEAR THE LOSS
FOR THE SAKE OF THE VILLAGE.
- BUT WHEN THE ARROW
LANDED ON OUR ROOF,
HE TOLD ME TO GO AND HIDE.
- SO HE FOUND ANOTHER CHILD
TO TAKE YOUR PLACE,
AND MEANWHILE YOU'RE IN HIDING?
- [SIGH] WHAT A STUPID,
SELFISH PARENT.
- I AGREE WITH YOU THERE.
- THAT'S WHY
YOU WANT TO SAVE HIM.
- HE'S ONE OF
MY VERY BEST FRIENDS.
WE GREW UP TOGETHER.
THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GONNA LET HIM TAKE MY PLACE.
- WELL, I HOPE YOU HAVE A BOAT.
- HUH?
- THAT DEMON HAS TO BE
EXTERMINATED.
I HAVE A REPUTATION TO UPHOLD.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THE WATER GOD BY MYSELF.
- YOU'RE STILL RECOVERING.
STOP TRYING TO ACT
SO TOUGH, SHOW-OFF.
I BET YOU CAN'T EVEN LIFT THAT
HEAVY WEAPON OVER YOUR HEAD YET.
- IS THAT A CHALLENGE?
- BRING IT ON ANYTIME.
- INUYASHA!
- LISTEN, WE ALL RECEIVED
PAYMENT FOR OUR SERVICES,
SO LET'S BAND TOGETHER
AND FINISH THE JOB.
- INUYASHA, STOP PICKING FIGHTS
WITH EVERYBODY.
- HUH! TELL THAT TO HER,
NOT ME.
SHE WANTS TO WORK ALONE
ALL THE TIME
AND DOESN'T WANT
TO JOIN OUR TEAM.
- THERE IT IS--
THE WATER GOD'S SHRINE GATE.
- THAT'S THE SHRINE I SAW
THIS AFTERNOON.
- THE HUMAN SACRIFICE
HAS ENTERED.
- [MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- GATEKEEPERS. HIDE.
- WHY SHOULD WE HIDE?
- NO!
- AAH!
- YOU'RE IN THE WAY.
- UHH!
- YAH!
HURRY. DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
WE'RE GOING IN.
- IS HE EVER STRONG!
- WE BROUGHT THE HUMAN
SACRIFICE, MASTER.
- COME CLOSER.
- [WHIMPERING]
- HMM.
YOUR HANDS ARE DIRTY
AND CALLUSED
FROM WORKING OUT
IN THE FIELDS.
THIS PROVES THAT YOU ARE NOT
THE HEADMAN'S SON.
WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS?
HOW DARE YOU TRY TO DECEIVE
THE WATER GOD, BOY?
- PLEASE,
O MIGHTY WATER GOD,
PLEASE EAT ME
AS YOUR SACRIFICE INSTEAD.
UNH!
- YOU HAVE DISHONORED ME
WITH YOUR LITTLE RUSE.
- [GRUNTING]
- I WILL TEAR YOU
LIMB FROM LIMB
AND SEND YOU BACK TO
THE VILLAGE--
BACK IN PIECES
WITH THE NEXT RAIN.
[RUMBLING]
- OHH!
- UHH!
- YOU BETTER GET OUT OF THE WAY!
MOVE IT!
- HOW DARE YOU CHARGE IN HERE?
THIS IS A SACRED HOUSE!
- AH, SHUT UP!
- [GRUNTING]
- A CRAB!
WHOA!
ALL THE GUARDS ARE JUST
A BUNCH OF FISH AND CRABS
PUT UNDER A SPELL.
- UHH!
DID I INTERRUPT DINNER?
- MASTER TARO?
- SUEKICHI! AAH!
- CALM DOWN.
- YOU'RE DRESSED LIKE
A DIRTY URCHIN,
BUT YOU'RE THE HEADMAN'S SON,
AREN'T YOU?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
NOW THAT YOU'VE GOT ME,
RELEASE SUEKICHI.
I'M THE REAL
HUMAN SACRIFICE.
- HUH? WHY'D YOU HIRE US
IF YOU'RE JUST GONNA
THROW YOURSELF AT HIM?
THE ONLY THING STRONG ABOUT YOU,
WATER GOD, IS YOUR SCENT.
YOU REEK OF DEMON!
AARRGGH!
UNH!
THE TETSUSAIGA
HAS BEEN TRANSFORMED BACK.
- A PETTY DEMON SWORD
LIKE YOURS
IS NO MATCH FOR THE POWER
OF THE TRIDENT OF AMAKOI.
YOU HAVE COMMITTED A GRAVE CRIME
IN DEFACING MY SHRINE.
YOU WILL PAY FOR THIS
WITH YOUR LIVES.
- HUH?
- [ALL GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
- I'M UNDERWATER.
KAGOME!
UNH!
- INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
- UHH!
- OHH!
- [COUGHING] HUH?
HE'S GOING TO TRY
TO EAT THE BOY.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
- [WHIMPERING]
AAAAHHH!
UHH!
- NOW'S MY CHANCE.
COME ON, HIT THE MARK!
- AAH!
UHH.
IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW CAN THIS BODY SUCCUMB
TO A HUMAN ARROW?
- COME ON!
SNAP OUT OF IT, WILL YOU?
- HUH?
- THANK YOU. YOU OK?
- YES.
- SUEKICHI!
- MASTER TARO!
- COME ON. HURRY!
- [GROANING AND HISSING]
- [PANTING]
- JUST KEEP ON RUNNING,
YOU GUYS,
AND INUYASHA
WILL CATCH UP WITH US.
- HOW DARE YOU INJURE MY ARM,
YOU IMPERTINENT WENCH?
I'M GOING TO SWALLOW YOUR SOUL.
- SANGO.
SANGO, WAKE UP!
- [MEOW]
- OH, NO.
SHE SWALLOWED TOO MUCH WATER.
I'LL HAVE TO BREATHE AIR
INTO HER.
- HMM?
[SMACK ECHOING]
- MY INTENTIONS
WERE HONORABLE.
- RIGHT.
WHERE AM I, ANYWAY?
- WE'RE OUTSIDE THE GATES
OF THE WATER GOD'S SHRINE.
I FOUND MYSELF HERE
WHEN I CAME TO.
[GASP] IS THAT INUYASHA?
- [GRUNTS]
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HELP.
DID YOU SAVE US
FROM DROWNING
IN THE FLOOD OF WATER
LIKE THIS, TOO?
- YES!
- BUT JUDGING FROM
YOUR APPEARANCE,
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU ARE SERVANTS
OF THE WATER GOD.
- THE WATER GOD IS NOTHING
BUT AN IMPOSTOR.
- HE USED TO BE
A SIMPLE WATER SPRITE LIKE US
AND LIVED HERE IN THE LAKE,
BUT HE RESORTED TO TRICKERY
TO GAIN POWER.
- HE SEALED THE REAL WATER GOD
IN THE CRAGGY ROCK OVER THERE.
THEN HE TOOK
THE TRIDENT OF AMAKOI AND,
WITH A GREAT DECLARATION,
FOOLED THE VILLAGERS
INTO THINKING HE WAS
THE WATER GOD.
- NOW I UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING.
THAT MEANS WE HAVE TO RESCUE
THE REAL WATER GOD.
- GET YOUR PRIORITIES STRAIGHT,
YOU IDIOT.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
[COUGHING]
I'M GONNA HEAD BACK
TO THE SHRINE NOW.
- HUH?
- SAVING KAGOME
HAS TO COME FIRST!
[SLOW, RHYTHMIC THUMPING]
- THE FOOTSTEPS
HAVE STOPPED.
[CREAKING]
- [GASP]
- I WILL DESTROY
YOU FIRST, WENCH.
- [GASP]
- ARE YOU GONNA LEAVE
INUYASHA ALONE
AND LET HIM DEAL WITH
THE WATER GOD ALL BY HIMSELF?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT INUYASHA.
HE CAN HANDLE THE WATER GOD
JUST FINE ON HIS OWN.
- ARE YOU SURE?
IS HE REALLY THAT STRONG?
- NOT ONLY IS HE STRONG,
HE'S ALSO VERY CUNNING.
HE'S NOT USUALLY SO HOSTILE
TO BE AROUND,
BUT I'M GUESSING THAT
IT'S HIS WAY OF HAVING
SYMPATHY FOR YOU.
HE THINKS THAT FIGHTING
WILL EASE YOUR PAIN,
AND THAT IS WHY HE'S ACTING
SO AGGRESSIVE.
HE'S SEEKING VENGEANCE FOR YOU.
BUT MAYBE I'M GIVING HIM
TOO MUCH CREDIT
AND READING TOO MUCH
INTO HIS BEHAVIOR.
- UHH!
- [GASP] INUYASHA!
- DAMN IT.
KAGOME, IS EVERYBODY SAFE?
- UH-HUH.
- HEY, THE WATER GOD
IS ESCAPING!
- [PANTING]
WHERE ARE YOU, WATER GOD?
AAH!
AAAH!
- INUYASHA!
- [GASPING]
YOU'RE SHOWING
YOUR TRUE COLORS NOW.
YOU'RE NOT THE WATER GOD.
YOU'RE A FAKE!
AND WITHOUT THAT TRIDENT,
YOU'RE BACK TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE FOOD CHAIN!
- HOW DARE YOU?!
- AAH!
[SCREAMING]
- [GRUNTING]
- I WONDER WHICH CAVE
THE REAL WATER GOD IS
BEING HELD CAPTIVE IN.
- WELL, IT HAS TO BE
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
- IS SOMEONE THERE?
- HUH?
- THE VOICE OF A YOUNG WOMAN.
- WHO'S THERE?
- I SEE. THE WATER GOD
IS ACTUALLY THE WATER GODDESS.
- HUH?
- JUST HURRY UP AND UNSEAL
THIS CAVE AND SET ME FREE.
- RIGHT AWAY.
UNH!
AAH!
- HUH?
[FOOTSTEPS]
- HELLO? GODDESS?
- IN HERE.
- UH...
WHA...
UH...
HA HA!
YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL BUT SO TINY.
IT WOULD BE A FIRST FOR ME,
BUT I'M CERTAINLY WILLING
TO GIVE IT A TRY.
- TRY WHAT?!
- UH, NOTHING.
RESIST ALL TEMPTATION.
- HA HA HA HA!
- I CAN'T BREATHE!
[GROANING]
- INUYASHA!
- HE'S NOT COMING UP!
- KAGOME!
- [GASP]
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THE WATER GOD
DRAGGED INUYASHA UNDERWATER
TO DROWN HIM.
- LET ME DOWN.
I SHALL SUBDUE THIS IMPOSTOR.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY, GODDESS.
- SHE'S THE WATER GOD?
- I COMMAND THE WATERS
TO PART!
- HUH? THAT'S...
- THE WATERS ARE PARTING!
- INUYASHA'S AT THE BOTTOM!
LOOK OUT!
- I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU FREED
THE WATER GODDESS,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
NOW I'M THE REIGNING WATER GOD.
- EVEN THOUGH
SHE'S THE REAL WATER GOD,
SHE'S POWERLESS WITHOUT
HER SACRED TRIDENT.
- PREPARE TO DIE!
- NOT SO FAST,
BOTTOM-FEEDER!
YAH!
- KIRARA!
- YOU FOOL!
NOW YOU SHALL FEEL THE AWESOME
AND POWERFUL WRATH
OF THE TRIDENT OF AMAKOI!
- THE SACRED TRIDENT
IS MAKING RAINCLOUDS.
- CATCH THIS, WATER SNAKE.
UHH!
HUH? AAH!
- SANGO!
- NOW DIE!
- SANGO! ARE YOU OK?
- INUYASHA!
- I'M TIRED OF LOOKING AT
YOUR SCALY HIDE, YOU BIG FAKER!
AAH!
DAMN IT! AAH!
- NO! INUYASHA!
- ENOUGH IS ENOUGH,
YOU OVERGROWN INCHWORM!
- THE TWISTER
IS HEADING FOR THE VILLAGE.
- THE WINDS ARE GONNA BLOW
THE WHOLE PLACE APART.
- CALMING A TWISTER
IS A SIMPLE MATTER.
I COULD DO IT IN MY SLEEP.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- THEN JUST DON'T
TALK ABOUT IT. DO IT!
- I WOULD BE HAPPY TO,
YOUNG MAN,
AS SOON AS YOU RETRIEVE
MY SACRED TRIDENT.
- INUYASHA?
- DON'T WORRY, GUYS.
IT'LL TAKE MORE THAN
THIS PATHETIC REPTILE
TO GET RID OF ME.
- STOP BRAGGING,
AND JUST HURRY UP
AND GET THE TRIDENT!
- YOU'D THINK SHE COULD SHOW
A LITTLE BIT OF CONCERN FOR ME.
AAH!
HERE, TAKE THE STUPID THING!
- I'LL GO GET IT.
- TAROMARU!
- I MUST SAVE THE VILLAGE,
OR I WON'T BE ABLE TO FACE
ALL THE FAMILIES
WHO LOST THEIR CHILDREN.
HUH?
UNH!
- MASTER TARO!
- PRETTY SLICK MANEUVERING
THERE, SANGO.
- THAT'S NOTHING.
- OK, I'M GOING DOWN
AND AIMING FOR HIS HEAD.
- GOTCHA.
DO IT, INUYASHA!
- I'M ON IT!
UNH!
TETSUSAIGA!
HYAH!
- [SHRIEKING]
- DON'T WORRY.
I'LL HANDLE THE CLEANUP.
HYAH!
- YAH!
[GRUNTS]
HERE YOU GO.
- WATER GODDESS,
PLEASE WORK YOUR MAGIC.
- HUH? SHE GOT BIGGER.
- CLOUDS, DISPERSE!
- [ALL GASP]
- DID THEY LEAVE US ALREADY?
- YES.
- I DIDN'T GET TO
THANK THEM PROPERLY.
EACH ONE OF THEM
RISKED THEIR LIVES
TO SAVE THIS VILLAGE
FROM THE FAKE WATER GOD.
- MAN, WE SPEND ALL OUR TIME
FIGHTING AN OVERGROWN SNAKE,
AND NO JEWEL SHARD.
- IT WASN'T ALL A WASTE.
WE HELPED OUT THE NEEDY.
- HEY, WHAT YOU GOT
IN THE CART, MONK?
- WELL, I MENTIONED TO
THE HEADMAN
THAT I WOULDN'T BE OPPOSED TO
TELLING THE VILLAGERS
THAT HIS SON ACTED WITH
TREMENDOUS BRAVERY,
AND FOR SOME REASON,
HE GAVE ME THESE GIFTS.
- YOU BLACKMAILED HIM INTO IT,
DIDN'T YOU?
- DOES HE ALWAYS PULL
STUNTS LIKE THIS?
- SOMETIMES.
- WHEN I GROW UP,
I WANT TO BE BRAVE AND HONORABLE
JUST LIKE THEM.
- I THINK WE SHOULD SELL THESE
THINGS OFF IN THE NEXT VILLAGE
AND HAVE A BIG PARTY
TO CELEBRATE.
- OH,
THAT'S THE LAST TIME I DO
ANY ACTS OF HUMAN KINDNESS
WITH YOU.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- THIS IS STRANGE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN MIROKU
SINCE THIS MORNING.
ACCORDING TO MYOGA,
MIROKU WAS LOOKING AT
HIS RIGHT HAND
WITH A SERIOUS EXPRESSION
LAST NIGHT.
THERE'S MORE OF
THOSE POISONOUS INSECTS!
IT MIGHT BE A TRAP
SET BY NARAKU.
MIROKU'S WIND TUNNEL
HAS BEEN INJURED,
AND HE'S SURROUNDED BY DEMONS.
INUYASHA, HURRY.
I THINK MIROKU PLANS
TO DIE FIGHTING.
NEXT TIME, "MIROKU FALLS INTO
A DANGEROUS TRAP."
SEE YOU SOON!