>> IT ALL STARTED WITH
THE SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING
FOR OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS
BETWEEN US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> THE PATH TO THE AFTERLIFE
IS OPEN, AND WE CHASED NARAKU
TO THE BORDER OF THE 2 WORLDS.
A DEMON PROTECTOR OF THE SACRED
SHARD AWAITS US IN THE GRAVEYARD
OF INUYASHA'S FATHER.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF
THE WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
"INUYASHA."
>> HA, HA, HA, HA!
WHAT'S THIS?
UH--AAH!
>> OH, DAMN YOU!
AH!
>> HOW HORRIBLE!
>> HE TAKES EVERY ADVANTAGE OF
THEM, THEN DOES THIS.
>> HA!
WHY DO YOU LOOK SO SURPRISED?
YOU WERE PLANNING TO DEFEAT
PRINCESS ABI AS WELL.
THE WAY I SEE IT, YOU SHOULD BE
GRATEFUL.
THANKS TO ME, THE PATH TO
THE BORDER IS OPEN.
YOU ARE ALL NOW ABLE TO TRAVEL
TO THE BORDER OF THE AFTERLIFE.
HMMM.
THE TIME HAS COME.
>> [GASPS]
>> HE CUT OFF TEKKEI'S HEAD!
>> A RIVER OF BLOOD.
>> THIS BLOOD WILL CONNECT TO
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT?
>> HA, HA, HA, HA!
HA, HA, HA, HA!
>> HUH?
NARAKU!
>> WHY ARE YOU JUST STANDING
THERE?
THIS RIVER OF BLOOD WON'T LAST,
AND THE PATHWAY WILL CLOSE
BEHIND ME.
>> HAH!
LIKE I DIDN'T KNOW THAT!
>> INUYASHA, WHAT ARE WE
WAITING FOR?
>> SANGO, LET'S FOLLOW HIM, TOO.
>> YOU MUSTN'T GO,
MASTER INUYASHA!
EVEN IF YOU ARE ABLE TO GET TO
THE BORDER ON THIS CURRENT,
HOW DO YOU INTEND TO COME BACK?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT NARAKU WILL
HAVE THE SAME PROBLEM.
>> THIS ISN'T THE TIME TO BE
WORRYING ABOUT HOW TO GET BACK.
>> MY THOUGHTS EXACTLY.
>> HUH?
AAH!
>> HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER,
SHIPPO?
>> THERE'S SOMETHING BACK THERE
THAT LOOKS LIKE A HUMAN FACE!
>> WHAT ON EARTH?
PRINCESS ABI'S MOTHER DRANK
HUMAN BLOOD.
THOSE FACES ARE PROBABLY
THE SOULS WHO BEAR A GRUDGE
TOWARD HER FOR THEIR DEATHS.
>> THINK HOW MANY PEOPLE WERE
KILLED UP UNTIL NOW,
JUST SO HE COULD GET HIS HANDS
ON THE JEWEL SHARD.
>> WE'VE GOT TO HURRY, AND BRING
THIS TO AN END QUICKLY!
>> RIGHT.
[GRUNTS]
>> OH, HOW LONG WILL THIS
JOURNEY LAST?
OHH.
HUH?
LORD SESSHOMARU,
WHAT COULD THAT BE?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU,
IT'S A GIANT BIRD!
>> MMM.
HUH?
AAH!
IT'S BEEN BEHEADED!
>> THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
A MASSIVE AMOUNT OF BLOOD,
YET THE SCENT HAS DISAPPEARED.
MM?
>> IT SEEMS YOU WERE TOO LATE
GETTING HERE, SESSHOMARU.
THIS ENTRYWAY HAS ALREADY OPENED
AND CLOSED AGAIN.
>> KAGURA!
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO, ANYWAY?
YOU'VE BEEN SHOWING UP A LOT
LATELY, AND I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW
LORD SESSHOMARU ISN'T THE LEAST
BIT INTERESTED IN YOU.
>> HUH?
>> OR...MAYBE HE IS.
>> THE ENTRYWAY?
THE ENTRYWAY TO WHERE, EXACTLY?
>> THAT'S UNUSUAL.
HE'S TAKEN THE BAIT.
TO THE PATH THAT LEADS TO
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT.
NARAKU AND INUYASHA HAVE ALREADY
GONE THROUGH.
>> FROM YOUR MANNER OF SPEAKING,
IT SEEMS THAT YOU KNOW
SOMETHING ELSE.
>> I DO KNOW SOMETHING ELSE--
ABOUT ANOTHER PATH, IN FACT.
IT'S DANGEROUS, THOUGH.
EVEN YOU MIGHT NOT BE ABLE
TO CROSS THAT PATH ALIVE.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
SOMETHING SEEMS WRONG HERE.
>> HUH?
>> IT'S A LIGHT!
>> IS IT THE EXIT?
KAGOME, YOU'D BETTER
HANG ON TIGHT!
[GRUNTING]
>> AH!
>> HUH?
I KNOW THIS PLACE.
>> AAH, AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> AAH!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HE ALMOST BLEW US AWAY
THAT TIME.
>> [SIGHS]
>> INUYASHA, ISN'T THIS PLACE--
>> YEAH.
GO THAT WAY!
>> OLD MAN.
>> THIS IS IT,
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT.
>> IT'S A DEMON GRAVEYARD.
>> SO IS THAT INUYASHA'S FATHER?
>> HUH?
IT'S ENORMOUS.
>> INUYASHA.
>> OK, THIS ISN'T THE TIME
TO BE SIGHTSEEING, KAGOME.
REMEMBER, NARAKU GOT HERE
BEFORE WE DID.
>> HMM.
>> DAMN THAT NARAKU.
KNOWING HIM, HE'LL PROBABLY TRY
TO LAY LOW UNTIL KAGOME FINDS
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> I CAN SENSE THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD.
INUYASHA!
INUYASHA, INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
[GASPING]
[GURGLING]
>> INUYASHA!
COME ON, SNAP OUT OF IT!
>> HUH?
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU BLANKED OUT FOR A MINUTE.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
WHY DID THAT VISION COME TO ME
OUT OF NOWHERE?
>> KAGOME, EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH, WE'RE OK.
>> [YELLING]
>> HUH?
>> AH!
[SCREECHES]
>> THOSE ARE SPEARS OF CRYSTAL!
>> AH!
WE'LL BE SKEWERED MEAT!
>> NARAKU'S GOTTA BE BEHIND
THIS!
UH!
>> THESE ARE SHARDS OF ADAMANT!
>> SHARDS OF ADAMANT?
YOU MEAN, AS IN DIAMONDS?
>> DIAMOND?
WHAT IN BLAZES IS THAT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE HARDEST
JEWEL IN THE WORLD, AND THESE
SPEARS ARE MADE OF ADAMANT!
>> INUYASHA, I DON'T SENSE
NARAKU'S DEMONIC AURA AT ALL.
>> THEN WHO THE HELL IS
BEHIND THIS?
AH!
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
SPEARS ARE SHOOTING OUT OF
MY OLD MAN'S GRAVE.
AH, DAMMIT!
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
>> THE LIGHT SPEARS HAVE STOPPED
FIRING!
>> [GASPS]
INUYASHA, THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARD!
IT'S INSIDE YOUR FATHER!
>> WHAT?
>> YOU THERE,
ARE YOU OF THE DEAD?
>> HUH?
>> YOU ARE GRAVE ROBBERS AFTER
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE?
AND WHY ARE YOU MAKING A NEST IN
THE BELLY OF SOMEONE'S FATHER?
>> FATHER, YOU SAY?
HMM.
ARE YOU SAYING YOU'RE THE SON
OF THE GREAT DOG DEMON?
>> MASTER INUYASHA, I THINK
I KNOW WHO THE SKULL CRYSTAL
REALLY IS.
HOSENKI,
AREN'T YOU MASTER HOSENKI?
IT'S ME, MYOGA.
DON'T YOU RECOGNIZE ME?
>> WHAT--HOSENKI?
>> EXACTLY.
THE DEMON WHO MADE THE BLACK
PEARL FOR INUYASHA LONG AGO.
>> SO, IT'S YOU, MYOGA.
THEN THIS YOUNG LAD MUST
BE INUYASHA.
>> YES!
MASTER INUYASHA IS NOT YOUR
ENEMY!
>> I RECALL THAT LONG AGO I MADE
THE BLACK PEARL AT YOUR FATHER'S
REQUEST.
HOWEVER, INUYASHA,
YOU PASSED THROUGH
THE BLACK PEARL ONCE TO COME
TO THIS WORLD.
HAVING FULFILLED ITS PURPOSE,
THE BLACK PEARL HAS LOST ITS
POWER AND RETURNED TO ITS PLACE
IN YOUR RIGHT EYE.
>> SO YOU DID IT!
YOU WERE THE ONE THAT MADE ME
HAVE THOSE VISIONS!
>> VISIONS?
THOSE WERE PROBABLY THOUGHTS
STILL LEFT IN THE BLACK PEARL.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> DIDN'T THE VISIONS
YOU'VE HAD TELL YOU TO LEAVE
THIS PLACE?
IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING,
ENTERING THE LAND OF THE DEAD
AGAIN IS NOT ALLOWED,
NO MATTER WHO YOU ARE.
>> CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
THERE IT IS!
HOSENKI HAS THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD.
COULD YOU TELL ME WHY YOU
BROUGHT THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
HERE?
>> HUH?
SO YOU HAVE IT AFTER ALL!
HAND IT OVER, AND YOU MIGHT
GET OFF EASY.
GIVE IT TO ME,
AND WE'LL GO BACK.
>> I CANNOT.
THAT IS BECAUSE IT WAS
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD'S DESIRE
TO COME TO THE LAND OF THE DEAD.
>> HUH?
>> THE SHARD'S DESIRE?
>> I AM THE DEMON WHO CONTROLS
JEWELS, AND I HAVE THE POWER
TO HEAR THEIR DESIRES.
WHEN I EXISTED IN
THE LAND OF THE LIVING
AND MY LIFE WAS NEARING ITS END,
A SACRED JEWEL SHARD CAME INTO
MY POSSESSION, AND THE SHARD
SPOKE TO ME AND SAID THAT
THE SACRED JEWEL MUST NEVER BE
ALLOWED TO BECOME WHOLE AGAIN.
MOST OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
ARE IN THE POSSESSION OF EVIL
MEN, AND ARE THUS TAINTED,
AND IF IT WERE TO BECOME MIXED
WITH THOSE, MY SHARD WOULD ALSO
BECOME TAINTED, AND THAT IS
PRECISELY WHY I MUST KEEP IT
HERE--IN THIS DEMON GRAVE
BEYOND THE REACH OF THE HANDS
OF EVIL.
IT WAS THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD'S
DESIRE TO COME WITH ME HERE.
>> [GASPS]
>> MASTER INUYASHA,
IT WOULD BE WISE TO BACK AWAY
FROM THIS PLACE.
LEAVE THE SHARD WITH HOSENKI.
>> HUH?
ARE YOU HALF ASLEEP OR
JUST STUPID?
NARAKU GOT HERE BEFORE US
AND HE'S STILL HERE.
HE'S HIDING SOMEWHERE,
WAITING FOR HIS CHANCE TO GET
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> NO ONE WILL TAKE THE SHARD
FROM ME.
>> HUH?
HOSENKI!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> WHAT'S THIS?
>> LOOK AT THE SKY!
>> SOMETHING EVIL IS ABOUT
TO HAPPEN.
>> HUH?
>> I SHALL NOT GO EASY ON YOU,
EITHER.
[ROARS]
>> HANG ON A MINUTE, HOSENKI!
WE COULD TALK THIS OUT,
DEMON TO DEMON!
>> [ROARS]
>> HUH?
UH!
KAGOME, YOU STAY HERE,
OUT OF THE WAY.
>> INUYASHA!
>> HEY, UGLY, BETTER LEARN
TO TELL THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
FRIEND AND FOE!
[GRUNTS]
AAH!
>> HOW COME THE TETSUSAIGA
ISN'T WORKING?
>> IT'S USELESS,
MASTER INUYASHA.
HOSENKI'S ARMS ARE MADE OF
HARDENED ADAMANT!
>> YOU'RE HERE, MYOGA?
I'M SURPRISED.
WHEN DID YOU GET BACK?
>> DAMMIT!
>> [ROARS]
>> THE ATTACKS ARE RELENTLESS.
INUYASHA HAS NOTHING TO LAND ON!
>> PLEASE, HOSENKI,
TELL ME YOU AREN'T SERIOUSLY
TRYING TO HARM MASTER INUYASHA!
>> OH!
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD!
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD!
BE CAREFUL, INUYASHA!
HOSENKI'S SACRED JEWEL SHARD
HAS SUDDENLY TURNED BLACK!
>> HUH?
>> HOW CAN THAT BE?
>> FROM WHAT WE KNOW,
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD TURNS
GOOD OR EVIL DEPENDING ON
THE HEART OF ITS POSSESSOR.
AND JUDGING BY HOSENKI'S STORY,
I'M NOT COMPLETELY SURE
HE BROUGHT THE SHARD HERE
OUT OF PERSONAL GREED.
>> I SENSE THE PRESENCE OF
TAINTED SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
AND IT'S HUGE!
IT MUST BE NARAKU'S.
>> NARAKU'S SHARDS ARE
INFLUENCING HOSENKI?
>> HEY, KAGOME, WHERE IS HE?
WHERE IS NARAKU HIDING?
>> I CAN'T TELL.
THE PRESENCE IS COMING FROM
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
I CAN'T TELL WHERE HE IS.
>> DID YOU HEAR THAT, HOSENKI?
YOU DON'T WANT TO HANG ON
TO THAT THING!
YOUR SOUL WILL BE CORRUPTED
BY THE TAINTED JEWEL SHARD.
GIVE IT UP NOW--
WHILE YOU STILL CAN!
>> DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
I'M NOT SO WEAK AS TO LOSE
MY SOUL TO A MINOR IRRITANT
AS THIS.
I WILL NOT GIVE IT UP TO ANYONE.
>> DAMN!
I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO TAKE IT BY FORCE.
HEY, HOSENKI, I'LL CUT
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD OUT
OF YOU MYSELF BEFORE YOUR SOUL
IS TOTALLY DEVOURED!
>> TAKE IT, IF YOU THINK
YOU CAN.
>> HIS WHOLE BODY IS TURNING
BLACK.
>> THE EVIL FROM THE SHARD MUST
BE CORRUPTING HIM.
>> HERE I COME!
>> MASTER INUYASHA,
GO EASY ON HIM!
HOSENKI IS AN OLD FRIEND OF
YOUR FATHER!
HE IS NOT A BAD DEMON!
>> I MIGHT HAVE GONE EASY IF
HE'D ONLY DONE WHAT I'D ASKED.
WIND SCAR!
>> OH!
>> DID I GET HIM?
HUH?
AH!
UH--
NOT AGAIN!
[PANTING]
[GURGLING]
[WHIMPERS]
I WON'T--I WON'T RUN AWAY!
>> INUYASHA?
>> [ROARS]
>> INUYASHA!
>> DAMN YOU TO HELL!
WIND SCAR!
>> THE WIND SCAR--IT DIDN'T
WORK ON HIM!
>> [ROARS]
>> I'VE GOT TO GET CLOSE TO
THE SHARD.
AH--AH!
>> [GRUNTS]
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
>> I'VE GOT TO STOP
HOSENKI'S ATTACK!
I KNOW!
IF I CAN PURIFY THAT
SHARD SOMEHOW--
MY ARROW WILL PROBABLY WORK!
GO!
ALL RIGHT, I GOT IT!
>> YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
>> OH!
I DIDN'T PURIFY THE SHARD!
>> KAGOME'S ARROW DIDN'T
EVEN WORK!
>> THE ARROW DIDN'T EVEN REACH
THE SHARD.
>> THAT BODY IS LIKE AN
IMPENETRABLE ARMOR.
>> THAT'S NOT ALL.
HOSENKI WAS A GREAT DEMON
WHO LIVED FOR A LONG TIME.
YOUR ARROW DOESN'T HAVE ENOUGH
SPIRITUAL POWER!
>> HMM.
ALL RIGHT, SO THE SPIRITUAL
POWER NEEDS TO BE STRONGER.
KIKYO'S ARROW MIGHT WORK.
AH!
WHY DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> [GRUNTS]
KIKYO'S ARROW REJECTED HER?
>> GIVE THIS ARROW TO KAGOME.
ONLY SHE CAN DETERMINE WHETHER
OR NOT SHE'LL BE ABLE TO USE IT.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
SO KAGOME DOESN'T HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES?
HUH?
UH!
HE'S COVERING A SPOT THAT
WAS HIT BY KAGOME'S ARROW!
KAGOME, AIM FOR THAT SAME SPOT
ONCE MORE!
>> WHY?
>> HURRY UP AND SHOOT!
>> ALL RIGHT, HANG ON!
>> JUST BECAUSE KAGOME'S ARROW
DIDN'T REACH THE SHARD
DOESN'T MEAN IT HAD NO EFFECT.
>> AH!
>> I'LL AIM FOR THE SAME SPOT.
WIND SCAR!
>> IT BROKE OPEN!
>> ALL RIGHT!
NOW I CAN GET THE SHARD.
>> YOU IMBECILES!
>> HUH?
>> [ROARS]
>> AH!
[MOANS]
>> INUYASHA!
>> YOU AND I--ALL OF US WERE
NOTHING BUT PUPPETS MANIPULATED
BY THE BLACK JEWEL.
>> INUYASHA...
OH, INUYASHA!
>> [MUSIC]
>> I FINALLY POSSESS THE LAST
OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> HOSENKI'S SHARD IS STOLEN
BY NARAKU!
>> FINALLY, HE'S COME OUT
OF HIDING.
THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR.
>> SESSHOMARU IS GUIDED BY
KAGURA TO THE SITE OF
THE SHOWDOWN.
>> TRYING TO SAVE YOUR
YOUNGER BROTHER.
WHAT A KIND SIBLING YOU ARE.
>> A HALF-DEMON LIKE YOU,
DEFILING MY FATHER'S GRAVE.
>> NEXT TIME,
FINAL BATTLE AT THE GRAVESIDE!
SESSHOMARU VERSUS INUYASHA.
>> THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN KILL
NARAKU IS SESSHOMARU.