- CAN YOU KILL THEM?
- YES, MASTER NARAKU.
- CAN YOU KILL INUYASHA,
MIROKU, AND SANGO?
- YES, MASTER NARAKU.
- I MADE HIM FORGET.
I ERASED ALL THE MEMORIES
OF HIS LIFE.
- HMM.
- BRING ME THE TETSUSAIGA,
INUYASHA'S PRECIOUS SWORD.
ONLY THEN SHALL I LET KOHAKU
HAVE ETERNAL LIFE.
- HMM. HUH?
HMM.
WHAT AM I DOING?
IF I GIVE THE SWORD TO NARAKU,
WHO KNOWS WHAT HE'LL DO?
HUH?
HMM.
[SIGH]
- HMM?
SANGO, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOTHING'S WRONG.
I JUST COULDN'T GET TO SLEEP.
- I KNOW I HAVE TO KILL HIM,
BUT I FEEL BADLY FOR YOU.
- I ALREADY EXPLAINED
TO YOU, INUYASHA,
HE IS NOT MY BROTHER.
THE LITTLE BROTHER I KNEW
COULD NEVER SLAUGHTER
AN ENTIRE VILLAGE.
IT WOULD GO AGAINST
HIS VERY SOUL.
I WILL PUT AN END TO NARAKU
AND THE IMPOSTOR.
- [GASP]
- HOW CAN YOU BE THAT SIMPLE?
IF KOHAKU LOOKS
EXACTLY THE SAME,
CAN YOU REALLY FORGET EVERYTHING
AND TURN YOUR HEART AGAINST HIM
THAT EASILY?
- DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME.
I AM A DEMON SLAYER.
I WON'T FALL FOR
NARAKU'S TRICKS.
[SIGH]
- IF I WAS IN YOUR POSITION,
I PROBABLY COULDN'T DO IT.
- HE ASKED SANGO
HOW SHE COULD TURN HER HEART
AGAINST SOMEONE
AND FORGET EVERYTHING
IF THEY LOOKED EXACTLY THE SAME.
I BET INUYASHA WAS THINKING
ABOUT KIKYO WHEN HE SAID THAT.
THAT'S WHY HE
SYMPATHIZES WITH HER.
- INUYASHA.
- HUH?
- BEST BE ON YOUR GUARD.
WE'RE COMPLETELY SURROUNDED.
- [PANTING]
- KOHAKU?
HMM.
- MIROKU, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
YOUR WIND TUNNEL
ISN'T COMPLETELY HEALED.
- BUT...
ALL RIGHT.
- FORGET IT, MIROKU.
DON'T RISK YOUR LIFE
OVER THIS VERMIN.
ALL I GOT TO DO IS
TAKE OUT THEIR RINGLEADER,
AND THEN THE REST OF THEM
ARE TOAST.
- [SHRIEKING]
- GET LOST, YOU PACK OF RODENTS!
YAH!
HYAH!
[GRUNTING]
YOU'RE GONNA NEED
TO FIGHT BETTER THAN THAT
IF YOU'RE GONNA TRY
TAKING ME OUT!
AARGH!
HYAH!
IT'S OVER!
- STOP IT!
PLEASE DON'T KILL HIM!
- HUH?
YAH!
- UNH!
AAH!
- DAMN IT, ANYWAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I CAVED IN.
IT'S OK TO KILL HIM.
HE'S JUST ANOTHER TRAP
SET BY NARAKU.
I SHOULD KILL HIM!
I HAVE TO!
- [GROAN]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU SHOULD KILL ME.
I DESERVE TO DIE.
- WHAT?
- [GASP]
- I KILLED THEM ALL.
FATHER, OUR FRIENDS,
AND THE VILLAGERS--
I SLAUGHTERED THEM ONE BY ONE.
IT'S TRUE.
THAT'S WHY I SHOULDN'T BE
ALLOWED TO LIVE.
- UNH!
- HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HITTING YOURSELF?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO PROVE?
- HE'S TRYING TO TAKE
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD OUT.
HE'S SLASHING HIMSELF TO BITS!
- BUT THE JEWEL SHARD
EMBEDDED IN HIS BACK
IS WHAT SUSTAINS HIS LIFE.
IF THE SHARD IS LOOSENED
AND TAKEN OUT OF HIS BODY,
KOHAKU WILL DIE INSTANTLY.
DON'T DO IT!
- HUH?
SANGO?
- SANGO.
- SANGO?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, SANGO?
- HMM.
- HUH?
IS HE TESTING ME?
DOES HE REALLY BELIEVE
I WILL STEAL THE TETSUSAIGA
FROM INUYASHA
AND TAKE IT TO HIM?
WHAT DO I DO?
[GRUNT]
[GROWL]
KILALA!
- WAIT! SANGO!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
- I DON'T HAVE AN OPTION.
THIS IS THE ONLY THING I CAN DO.
THIS IS WHAT I TRULY WANT.
UNH!
- LET'S GO, INUYASHA!
WHY ARE YOU GUYS
JUST STANDING THERE?
MIROKU?
- HE HAS THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
- I CAN STILL SMELL HIS BLOOD.
YEAH, THAT'S HIM.
KOHAKU'S SCENT
IS STILL CLOSE BY.
I CAN FOLLOW IT.
- NARAKU'S CALLING HIM, I BET.
- I CAN'T USE MY WIND TUNNEL,
AND THE TETSUSAIGA IS STOLEN.
- WHO CARES?
I'LL PUNCH HIM OUT.
I STILL HAVE MY FISTS. HA!
- HMM.
- UNH.
THIS CASTLE.
[GROWLS]
KOHAKU? KOHAKU!
- FIRST, PUT DOWN YOUR WEAPON.
- NARAKU!
- WELL DONE, SANGO.
GOOD WORK.
YOU BROUGHT ME
INUYASHA'S SWORD,
THE TETSUSAIGA,
AS PROMISED.
- LET ME SEE KOHAKU.
I WILL ONLY HAND OVER THE SWORD
AFTER I SEE HIM.
HUH?
NARAKU, TURN KOHAKU BACK
TO HIS FORMER SELF IMMEDIATELY!
- KILLING ME WON'T HELP.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT ALREADY.
THIS IS THE FAULT OF
THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL.
DEMONS AND EVIL HUMANS
DESIRE THE JEWEL,
AND OUT OF THAT DESIRE,
DEMONS ATTACKED YOUR VILLAGE.
THAT'S WHY YOUR FATHER
WAS KILLED.
THAT'S WHY YOUR BROTHER KOHAKU'S
SOUL NOW WANDERS IN DARKNESS.
IT'S ALL PART OF THE CURSE
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
- STOP LYING!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO KILLED
MY FATHER AND COMRADES!
YOU COVETED THE STUPID JEWEL!
YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR EVERYTHING!
- PEOPLE DIE BECAUSE OF
THE POWER OF THE SACRED
SHIKON JEWEL,
AND PEOPLE LIVE
BECAUSE OF ITS POWER.
THERE'S NO REASON WHY YOU SHOULD
DESPISE THE SACRED JEWEL
AS MUCH AS YOU DO.
REMEMBER, KOHAKU WAS REVIVED
BECAUSE OF THE JEWEL'S POWER.
YOU MADE A PROMISE TO
EXCHANGE THE SWORD
FOR KOHAKU'S LIFE.
SO, WHAT WILL YOU DO?
- I DESPISE YOU!
I MADE NO PROMISE!
UNH!
YOU WANT MY ANSWER?
HERE IT IS!
UNH! YAH!
HUH?
[GRUNT]
IT'S YOU...
THE YOUNG LORD OF THE CASTLE.
- KAGEWAKI WAS A NOBLE LORD.
HE GAVE ALL THE DEMON SLAYERS
PROPER BURIALS.
AH, YES, AND I WAS THE ONE
WHO ORDERED FOR YOUR CARE
AFTER THE MASSACRE.
- YOU KILLED HIM!
- KAGEWAKI IS STILL ALIVE--
AT LEAST, ACCORDING TO THOSE
I FOOLED INTO THINKING I AM HIM.
- DAMN YOU!
UNH! UNH!
DIE!
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
KILALA!
OH, NO. KILALA, WHAT'S WRONG?
- NOTHING CAN SURVIVE
AN ATTACK OF MY POISON GAS.
THAT ALSO INCLUDES YOU, SANGO.
- WHAT? AAH!
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
- WELL, SANGO, WILL YOU AGREE TO
BE MY SERVANT HERE WITH KOHAKU?
I REMEMBER
KAGEWAKI'S LAST COMMAND.
HE ASKED YOU TO
RETURN TO THE CASTLE.
- [GASP]
ME BE YOUR SERVANT?
IN YOUR DREAMS.
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH, NARAKU.
MY ONLY GOAL IS TO DESTROY YOU.
I WILL AVENGE MY COMRADES.
I WILL KILL YOU!
- KOHAKU, COME.
- HUH?
HUH?
- AND NOW, SISTER, GOOD-BYE.
- KOHAKU.
- THE CASTLE!
- THIS IS IT.
THIS MUST BE
WHERE NARAKU IS HIDING.
- AAH!
- THAT WAS SANGO'S VOICE.
- DAMN IT!
- [SANGO GRUNTING]
KOHAKU.
KOHAKU, RESIST NARAKU.
- YES, SANGO. KILL HIM.
KILL YOUR BROTHER
WITH YOUR OWN HANDS.
SLAUGHTER HIM
AND THEN BURN
WITH THE DESIRE TO LIVE.
PRAY TO CONTINUE
WANDERING IN THE WORLD
AND VOW TO DO WHATEVER YOU CAN
TO SURVIVE.
WHEN YOU KILL KOHAKU
AND WHEN YOU ARE
BATHED IN HIS BLOOD,
THE SACRED JEWEL
WILL GLOW BRIGHTER
WITH THE POWER OF THE DARK.
THE MORE SULLIED IT IS,
THE MORE BEAUTIFUL
THE SACRED JEWEL BECOMES.
- KILL YOU?
WHAT MAKES HIM THINK
I'M ABLE TO KILL YOU?
I CAN'T.
KOHAKU.
- HUH?
HUH. MY SISTER.
- SANGO?
- SANGO!
- OH, NO! KILALA, ARE YOU OK?
- [GRUNTS]
- HE MADE HER BROTHER
DO THIS TO HER?
- AWFUL. HOW COULD HE?
- NARAKU! SHOW YOURSELF!
WHERE ARE YOU?
- KOHAKU KILLED HIS FATHER
AND HIS FELLOW VILLAGERS.
HE MASSACRED AN ENTIRE TOWN.
YET HIS SISTER SAYS
SHE CANNOT KILL HIM.
SHE LOVES HER BROTHER
MORE DEARLY THAN
SHE LOVES HER OWN LIFE.
HOW CAN THIS BE?
I DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
- HUH?
KOHAKU?
- YOU'LL BE ABLE TO GAIN
FULL CONSCIOUSNESS SOON.
- INUYASHA, THIS IS WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU 50 YEARS AGO.
NARAKU TRIED TO SET YOU UP
AGAINST THE ONE YOU LOVE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- NARAKU TRIED TO MAKE SANGO
HATE HER BROTHER.
HE HOPED THAT
SHE WOULD KILL HIM.
THEN THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
IN HIS BACK
WOULD BECOME EVEN MORE EVIL.
- HE TRICKED KIKYO AND INUYASHA
THE SAME WAY,
MADE THEM HATE
AND BETRAY EACH OTHER
SO THEY'D FIGHT.
THAT'S SO EVIL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'D DO THAT ON PURPOSE.
KIKYO DIED SO THAT
THE SACRED JEWEL
WOULD REMAIN DORMANT.
SANGO REFUSED
TO FIGHT HER BROTHER
FOR THE VERY SAME REASON.
NARAKU IS SUCH A TOTAL IDIOT.
SANGO WILL NEVER DO
WHAT HE WANTS HER TO DO.
SHE'S A KIND PERSON,
AND NO MATTER WHAT,
SHE WILL ALWAYS LOVE
HER LITTLE BROTHER.
- UNH!
A MIASMA!
- FOOLISH MORTALS.
NOW YOU CAN ALL DIE
IN THIS SEA OF POISON VAPOR.
- FATHER TOLD ME
HE'S BEEN WATCHING YOU,
AND HE THINKS YOU'RE GETTING
BETTER EVERY DAY, KOHAKU.
- REALLY?
-REALLY.
- THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER HEARD OF
FATHER PRAISING ME.
HA HA! MAKES ME FEEL
KIND OF EMBARRASSED.
- [GROAN]
- SANGO, YOU MUSTN'T MOVE YET.
- YEAH. STAY RIGHT
WHERE YOU ARE
AND DON'T BUDGE.
I GOT A THING OR TWO
TO CHEW YOU OUT FOR,
SO DON'T YOU DARE DIE ON ME,
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
- IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
BUT...
BUT I CAN GIVE YOU THIS.
- OHH.
- I KNOW.
NARAKU HAS JEWEL SHARDS.
I CAN FIND HIM!
OVER THERE!
NARAKU, TAKE THIS!
- UNH! AAH!
- WHAT?
- NARAKU!
YOU ARE TOTALLY DESPICABLE.
NOW...DIE!
- SHE'S ONLY A YOUNG GIRL.
WHY DOES SHE HAVE SO MUCH POWER?
SHE'S RENDERED THE VAPORS
HARMLESS SOMEHOW.
THIS KIND OF POWER ONLY BELONGS
TO THE PRIESTESS KIKYO.
CAN'T BE.
- I WON'T LET YOU GO,
EVEN IF YOU BEG FOR FORGIVENESS.
HA!
- THIS IS EXACTLY LIKE
KIKYO'S ENCHANTED ARROW.
DON'T TELL ME THIS GIRL IS...
- SHE DID IT!
- KAGOME PURGED THE MIASMA
AND PIERCED NARAKU.
- KAGOME!
- AAH!
- DON'T LET GO
OF KILALA, SHIPPO.
HOLD ON!
- AAH!
KOHAKU!
- [GRUNTING]
EH?
HUH? OH.
- AH.
THE CASTLE DISAPPEARED!
- IT WAS A PHANTOM CASTLE.
- LOOK.
- HUH?
DO YOU THINK NARAKU ESCAPED?
- MM-HMM.
HE MUST HAVE.
I DON'T SEE ANY JEWEL SHARDS.
- DAMN IT.
- I'M SORRY.
I COULDN'T KILL HIM.
- NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE, KAGOME.
WE SHOULD BE THANKING YOU.
WITHOUT YOU,
WE'D ALL BE DEAD BY NOW.
- KAGOME, I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
FIGHT LIKE THAT BEFORE.
IT WAS ALMOST AS GOOD AS ME.
- LISTEN, INUYASHA.
WE HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING WE CAN
TO DESTROY NARAKU,
NO MATTER HOW HARD
WE HAVE TO WORK.
WE'VE GOT TO PULL TOGETHER
AS A TEAM.
- DON'T TRY TO
MOVE AROUND, SANGO.
YOU'RE BADLY HURT.
- SANGO, WAIT!
- SOMEBODY HELP ME STOP HER!
SHE'S TRYING TO GET UP AND WALK!
- SANGO, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
REST A WHILE.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
- I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T STAY WITH YOU
ANY LONGER.
- SANGO, WE ALL UNDERSTAND THAT
NARAKU WAS THREATENING YOU
WITH THE LIFE OF YOUR BROTHER
IF YOU DIDN'T
GIVE HIM OVER THE SWORD.
- EXACTLY! I'LL END UP
BETRAYING YOU AGAIN!
AS LONG AS NARAKU
STILL CONTROLS KOHAKU...
- BUT, SANGO, PLEASE...
- SO WHAT DO YOU INTEND TO DO,
GO AFTER NARAKU ON YOUR OWN?
YOU'LL NEVER SUCCEED THAT WAY.
- I DON'T HAVE
ANY OTHER CHOICE, MIROKU.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
WE'LL ALL WORK TOGETHER
AS A TEAM
AND TRY TO SAVE YOUR BROTHER.
- YOU NEED MORE THAN ONE PERSON
TO HANDLE THAT KIND OF OPPONENT.
- NOW THAT THAT'S SETTLED,
LET'S TEND TO YOUR WOUNDS.
- BUT WHY WOULD YOU
STILL HELP ME?
- WILL YOU STOP WHINING, SANGO?
WE WANT YOU TO STICK WITH US
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
A HALF-BAD FIGHTER,
AND THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT!
- INUYASHA, I'M IMPRESSED.
- YOU SEE? EVEN INUYASHA
WANTS YOU TO STAY,
AND THAT'S SOMETHING
COMING FROM A GUY
WHOSE SWORD YOU STOLE
SO EASILY--
- DON'T SAY THAT!
IT MAKES ME SOUND LIKE
A STUPID HALF-WIT!
- I'M JUST SAYING YOU'RE
A VERY GENEROUS PERSON,
THAT'S ALL.
- SANGO, DON'T YOU
LIKE US ANYMORE?
- OF COURSE I DO,
BUT IT'S ALL MY FAULT
THAT THIS HAPPENED,
AND I MIGHT END UP
DOING SOMETHING LIKE THIS
TO ALL OF YOU AGAIN.
BUT...
[CRYING]
- POOR SANGO.
THIS WHOLE THING MUST HAVE BEEN
HEARTBREAKING FOR HER.
IT'S GONNA BE OK, SANGO.
I PROMISE.
WE'RE HERE WITH YOU NOW.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- WE JUST HEARD ABOUT AN HERB
THAT WILL HELP KILALA.
SHE WAS POISONED
WHEN SHE BIT INTO NARAKU
AND IS REALLY ILL.
SO INUYASHA AND I GO OUT
IN SEARCH OF THIS
HEALING HERB GARDEN,
AND WE COME ACROSS A HUGE DEMON
WORKING IN THE FIELD.
HE'S OBVIOUSLY REALLY STRONG,
AND HE LOOKS FIERCE
AND DANGEROUS,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S SOMETHING DIFFERENT
ABOUT THIS DEMON.
HIS EYES HAVE
A KINDNESS TO THEM.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!