[GASP]
- JUST THINK OF IT
AS A HIDING PLACE.
I'LL EVEN COME BACK
AND DIG YOU UP,
IF I REMEMBER.
- DO YOU PROMISE?
DO YOU SWEAR NOT TO FORGET?
[DOG BARKING]
- COME ON.
DON'T TELL ME
YOU BELIEVE HER STORY.
- HMM.
- BUT IT IS TRUE!
KAGOME FELL DOWN THE WELL,
AND THEN A MONSTER CAME UP
AND KIDNAPPED HER.
- THERE IS A CERTAIN LEGEND
OF THE BONE EATER'S WELL.
SINCE ANCIENT DAYS,
WHATEVER'S INSIDE
HAS CONSUMED THE CORPSES
OF MONSTERS.
BUT WHAT IF THE CONTINUUM
OF TIME-SPACE
IS ITSELF DISRUPTED?
- [MEOW]
- THAT'LL STOP YA.
[CHUCKLES]
[WHIRRING]
- CLOSED IT OFF?
- YUP.
WE NEEDN'T WORRY ABOUT ANY MORE
VISITORS FROM THERE.
I USED SPECIAL SPIRIT WARDS
JUST IN CASE.
- HMM.
- UHH.
[SNIFFING]
THAT'S HER, ALL RIGHT.
I'D KNOW HER ANYWHERE.
WHY'D SHE LEAVE HER CLOTHES?
SHE DID IT.
SHE WENT BACK TO HER OWN WORLD.
THROUGH HERE, WAS IT?
UHH.
[DOG BARKING]
- AHH, IT'S SO GOOD TO BE HOME
IN MY OWN BED.
WAS I REALLY THERE,
IN THAT WEIRD FEUDAL JAPAN?
- ONLY BY WORKING TOGETHER
WILL THE 2 OF YE
BE ABLE TO RECOVER THE SHARDS
OF THE JEWEL.
- OH, YOU NAUGHTY, NAUGHTY GIRL.
YOU SHATTERED THE JEWEL.
AND WHAT ABOUT THE GIRL,
THE ONE WITH THE HAIR?
WHAT DID SHE WANT?
DUH, THE JEWEL, OF COURSE.
[SIGH]
WHAT IF SHE WON'T GIVE IT BACK?
I CAN ALREADY HEAR INUYASHA.
- I NEVER ASKED FOR YOUR HELP.
GO HOME.
YOU ONLY SLOW ME DOWN, ANYWAY.
- HA. THAT'S RIGHT.
OH, WHAT AM I WORRYING
ABOUT HIM FOR?
THAT'S IT, THEN.
CHAPTER CLOSED.
- AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
IT WAS JUST A FAIRY TALE.
- KAGOME, IT'S DINNERTIME,
PLUS, YOUR FRIEND'S
ON THE PHONE.
- COMING!
- [MEOW]
- GRANDPA, THOSE THINGS
WILL STAY ON, RIGHT?
- 'COURSE THEY WILL.
HAVE A LITTLE FAITH, WILL YOU?
- IF THERE'S ONE THING I KNOW,
IT'S SPIRITS.
- AHH! REAL FOOD, REAL FOOD...
- I'LL DEFEND YOU
TO MY LAST BREATH, KAGOME,
SO DON'T YOU WORRY.
- I DON'T THINK SHE HEARD YOU.
- [SOBBING]
- AHH, WHAT A WONDERFUL TIME
TO BE ALIVE.
OH, I CAN'T WAIT TO--
- I--INUYASHA?
- IDIOT!
WHO TOLD YOU YOU COULD GO HOME?
- UH--WHAT--UH, WHERE DID YOU--
- THROUGH THE WELL, OF COURSE!
- THE WELL?
BUT THE WELL IS--
- YOU LIE!
I MADE THOSE
SPIRIT WARDS MYSELF.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD HAVE--
- WELL, I HATE TO BREAK IT
TO YOU, OLD MAN,
BUT THEY DON'T WORK.
- [SCREAMING]
- GRANDPA.
- COME ON, YOU.
WE'RE LEAVING.
- NO, AND YOU CAN'T MAKE ME.
- STAY RIGHT THERE.
- NOW WHAT?
- MOM, I--
- YOUR EARS.
ARE THEY REAL?
- ME NEXT!
ME NEXT!
- UH, MOM,
THAT'S NOT REALLY COOL.
THOUGH I DID IT, TOO, BUT...
INUYASHA, DO YOU SEE THAT?
- I DON'T SEE NOTHIN.'
- A HAIR.
ON YOUR SHOULDER, SEE?
[GASP]
IT MOVED.
- KAGOME, YOUR HAND.
- WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S HERE.
[GASP]
ONLY I CAN SEE IT.
- BUT SEEING ALONE
IS NOT ENOUGH.
[GASP]
- THAT GIRL WITH THE HAIR.
YURA.
OH, NO.
[WIND BLOWING]
[GASP]
HAIR!
LOTS AND LOTS OF IT.
- THE OLD CRONE WAS RIGHT.
YOU DO HAVE THE SIGHT.
- YOU DID IT!
THE HAIR FOLLOWED YOU,
SO IT CAME HERE!
- KAGOME!
- ARE YOU OK?
- DON'T COME IN!
[GASP]
I'VE GOT TO STOP IT COMING OUT.
AAH! IN FRONT OF YOU!
- WHERE? HERE?
UHH!
HUH...
HUH! YAA!
UHH...UH!
UHH!
- OPEN THE DOOR! NOW!
- KAGOME!
- UHH!
UHH!
- IT REGROWS, EVEN CUT!
PLUS, THERE'S SO MUCH OF IT!
[GROWLING]
[GASP]
- THAT'S IT.
THAT ONE STRAND OF HAIR
CONTROLS IT ALL.
UHH.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- HERE. DO YOU SEE IT?
CUT THIS ONE RIGHT HERE.
- WHICH ONE?
THIS ONE?
- INUYASHA CAN'T SEE IT.
I'LL HAVE TO HELP.
- LIKE THIS.
UHH.
- I SEE IT!
UHH!
IT PULLED BACK IN.
- THAT'S NOT GOOD.
YURA'S ALREADY GOT
MY PART OF THE JEWEL,
SO WHY'D SHE DO THIS?
UNLESS IT'S ME AND INUYASHA
SHE'S AFTER.
LET'S GO.
RIGHT NOW.
- BUT I THOUGHT THAT
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO GO BACK.
- I DON'T, BUT I HAVE TO.
- WHAT?
- MOM, SOTA, GRANDPA.
IF I STAY, THEY'LL BE IN DANGER.
HUH?
- IT'S MADE WITH HAIR
OF THE FIRE RAT.
YOU'LL HAVE SOME PROTECTION,
AT LEAST.
- UH, THANK YOU.
- YEAH, WELL, IF YOU WEREN'T
SO WEIRD-LOOKING,
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN NEED IT.
- YOU SHOULD TALK, DOG BOY.
- UHH. YEAH, YEAH, WHATEVER.
YOU READY?
- MM-HMM.
- GRR.
- THEY'LL BE BACK ANY MINUTE.
ONLY WE WON'T LET THEM RUN AWAY
THIS TIME, WILL WE?
[SOBS]
[CHUCKLES]
- HEAR ME, INUYASHA.
KAGOME TRULY IS KIKYO REBORN.
YET THAT WILL AID THEE
BUT LITTLE
IF SHE KNOWS NOT HER OWN POWER.
HELP HER, INUYASHA,
TO FIND HERSELF.
- BE CAREFUL.
THERE'S HAIR INSIDE HERE, TOO.
- UHH. SO YOU'RE SAYING
WHAT YURA IS REALLY AFTER
IS JUST US.
WELL, DUH.
I MEAN, WHY ELSE,
IF SHE ALREADY HAS
MY PIECE OF THE SACRED JEWEL?
- YOUR PIECE OF THE--
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
- I CAN SEE A LOT
OF HAIR IN THERE,
BUT ALL WE NEED TO WORRY ABOUT
IS THE MAIN ONE.
IF WE FOLLOW IT,
IT'LL LEAD STRAIGHT TO HER.
I'M SURE OF IT.
THERE!
- GOT IT!
- YE MUST BOTH WORK TOGETHER.
YE NEED KAGOME, INUYASHA,
AND KAGOME, YE NEED HIM.
FORGET YE DIFFERENCES FOR NOW,
AND BE AS ONE.
- UHH!
UHH.
- UH!
- A BONFIRE.
- WHERE ARE THEIR HEADS?
[GRUMBLES]
- THEY'RE GUYS FROM THE VILLAGE,
OR THEIR BODIES, ANYWAY.
LOOKS LIKE THEIR TOPS
CAME CLEAN OFF.
NOW WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I BETTER NOT HEAR YOU
SAY YOU'RE SCARED
OR YOU WANT TO GO HOME.
- ACTUALLY, I THOUGHT
I'D BORROW THESE.
IF WE DON'T STOP HER NOW,
EVEN MORE WILL DIE.
- YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT GONNA HIT.
WHY BOTHER?
- I JUST NEED PRACTICE.
- PRACTICE?
DON'T YOU MEAN "LEARN"?
- I'LL DO IT.
I REALLY THINK THAT I CAN!
- HMPH. THEN AGAIN,
WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE SHE'LL DO IT AFTER ALL.
- THEY'RE CLOSER.
LOTS CLOSER.
[THUNDER]
- UHH...UHH!
- THEY'RE HERE!
- UHH!
- FROM THE LEFT! FROM THE RIGHT!
- OK! HEY!
- AAH!
THERE'S TOO MANY.
YOU NEED TO HELP.
- ME?
I THOUGHT THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE HERE.
YOU'RE REALLY NOT GOOD FOR MUCH,
ARE YA?
- LEFT! LEFT!
- UHH!
- BEHIND!
UHH! GIVE ME A BREAK!
- UHH!
UHH...
- HUH?
- AAH!
[SCREAM]
- INUYASHA!
- UHH!
HUH?
- A GIANT HAIR BALL?
YURA'S HIDING PLACE.
- OH, MY,
LOOK AT THE CUTE DOGGIE.
[GRUNTING]
- YOU MUST BE INUYASHA.
- AND YOU MUST BE
YURA OF THE HAIR.
HOW'D YOU KNOW MY NAME?
- LET'S JUST SAY
A LITTLE BIRDIE TOLD ME.
EVERYONE'S SAYING
HALF-DEMON INUYASHA
IS PLAYING FETCH WITH SOME
REINCARNATED SHRINE MAIDEN.
- ME?
WITH THAT HALF-WIT HUMAN
DOWN THERE?
NOTHING DOING!
OH?
YOU'RE BOTH HALF-WITS TO ME.
JUST LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE
TO THE POOR JEWEL.
[GROWLING]
- THAT'S THE JEWEL PIECE
SHE STOLE FROM ME.
- ONCE YOU TWO HERE
HAVE BEEN WRAPPED UP,
I'LL GO AND FIND THE REST
FOR MYSELF.
- YOU, TAKE CARE OF ME?
[GRUNTING]
WHEN THIS IS OVER, YOU'RE GOING
TO WISH YOU'D NEVER MET ME
OR EVER HEARD MY NAME!
UHH! YAA!
AAH! AH!
- UHH.
- NOW WE'RE THE SAME.
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
UHH!
NO, NOT THIS AGAIN.
- SUCH PRETTY HAIR,
BUT YOU REALLY HAVEN'T
CARED FOR IT VERY WELL.
OH, LOOK AT THE SPLIT ENDS.
- GET OFF OF ME!
AAH!
UHH...OHH...
- INUYASHA!
- UHH.
[CHUCKLES]
MMM.
- I'M GOING TO CUT YOU
INTO LITTLE PIECES.
[CHUCKLES]
[SLURP]
I'M GOING TO CUT YOU
INTO LITTLE PIECES.
[GROWLING]
- UHH!
- AH!
- GET HIM DOWN,
RIGHT NOW.
NEXT TIME, I WON'T MISS.
I PROMISE.
- THE GIRL WHO FELL IN THE WELL.
- YOU HEARD ME.
- OOH, I THINK SHE
WANTS YOU BACK, INUYASHA.
WHAT A SWEET WIDDLE DOGGIE
YOU MUST BE.
- I TOLD YOU TO HIDE,
NOT DRAW ATTENTION TO YOURSELF!
- OF COURSE, HER HAIR'S NOT
SO PRETTY AS YOURS, INUYASHA,
BUT THEN...WASTE NOT, WANT NOT.
- NOT SO PRETTY AS HIS, HUH?
WHAT WOULD YOU KNOW
ABOUT IT, ANYWAY?
YOU LIVE IN A WORLD WHERE
THEY DON'T EVEN HAVE SHAMPOO!
AAH!
- HUH...AAH!
WOULD YOU WATCH WHERE
YOU'RE AIMING
THAT THING, PLEASE!
[GASP]
- OH, NO!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
- THOSE GUYS WE SAW
FROM THE VILLAGE.
- I'LL BE PUTTING YOU
IN HERE, TOO,
ONCE I SEPARATE THAT PRETTY HAIR
FROM YOUR HEAD.
IT'S WASTED ON YOU, ANYWAY.
FOR ONE THING, FIRST,
THAT WOMAN OVER THERE
HAS TO DIE.
[GASP]
- UHH!
- OHH!
- THERE.
HOT ENOUGH FOR YOU?
YOU'LL FEEL THE HEAT
RIGHT DOWN TO YOUR BONES.
[COUGHING]
- HELP ME.
- AWW.
THAT'S FOR EMPTYING OUT MY LAIR.
- HUH!
- PITY THERE'LL BE
NOTHING LEFT BUT ASH.
- COME ON!
- POOR THING.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
PETS OUGHT NEVER BE ALLOWED
TO OUTLIVE THEIR MASTERS.
YAAA!
- UHH!
YAHH!
BLADES OF BLOOD!
[GASP]
- OH, NO!
UHH...
- AAH!
- ITS LOOSENING UP.
- THAT'S NO FAIR!
THERE.
HOW'D YOU LIKE THAT?
SERVES YOU RIGHT!
- I DO WISH YOU'D
USE SOME RESTRAINT
WHEN ADDRESSING A LADY.
WERE YOU BROUGHT UP
IN A DOGHOUSE?
[LAUGHTER]
- HEADS UP.
[MOANING]
- UHH!
[GRUNT]
UHH!
- STAY STILL.
IT'S MUCH HARDER TO HIT
WHEN YOU MOVE.
- YEAH, I'LL JUST
BET IT IS!
[GROWLING]
UHH!
[GRUNT]
[CHUCKLES]
HALF-DEMON, HALF-POWER.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
- UHH.
WHY, YOU...
- DISAPPOINTED?
I'LL BET YOU WERE
HOPING TO USE THIS
TO BECOME ALL-DEMON.
- THE JEWEL OF FOUR SOULS.
- NOW, STAY STILL.
- IF I DON'T GET A CLEAN CUT,
YOUR BLOOD WILL STAIN
THAT PRETTY SILVER HAIR
OF YOURS.
- DON'T YOU WISH!
- UHH!
- HUH.
THAT'LL TEACH YA.
UHH!
- WHY, I NEVER.
A HALF-DEMON I JUST MET
STICKING HIS HAND IN MY CHEST?
- WH--WHY ISN'T SHE DEAD?
- PLUS THERE'S THE FACT
YOU STOLE MY JEWEL.
NOW I HAVE BECOME CROSS.
- HER WEAK SPOT.
WHERE IS IT?
[CHUCKLES]
- HUH?
HMM.
- UHH...UHH...UHH.
- THAT GIRL!
UHH!
- AHH! AHH! OH!
- HUH.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE LOOKED AWAY!
- AAH!
UHH--UHH.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT DOES IT!
- UHH! AHH!
HUH!
WHEN I TOOK YOUR HAND,
IT WAS LIKE YOU BROKE A NAIL,
BUT NOW YOU SEEM MAD FOR REAL.
WHAT ARE YOU HIDING
THAT YOU'RE SO WORRIED ABOUT?
[GASP]
- INUYASHA!
IT'S THAT RED SKULL UP THERE!
CONCENTRATE ON THAT!
- WHAT RED SKULL?
- UHH!
- OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
UHH! UHH!
- STOP PULLING MY HAIR!
- AAH!
- UHH!
WHOA!
[WHIMPERING]
- YOU'RE TANGLING IT ALL UP!
[GASP]
AAH!
- GOT YOU!
[SCREAMING]
UHH...UHH!
UHH!
HUH?
- WHAT ARE YOU?
WHY DON'T YOU BLEED?
- SHE'S RIGHT.
WHY WASN'T MY ARM CUT OFF,
AND WHY WASN'T I BURNED?
- IT'S MADE WITH HAIR
OF THE FIRE RAT.
WE'LL HAVE SOME PROTECTION,
AT LEAST.
INUYASHA.
- EVEN FROM HERE,
YOU LOOK MORTAL ENOUGH TO ME.
LET'S PUT YOU TO THE TEST.
UHH!
[CHOKING]
[LAUGHS]
- BLADES OF BLOOD!
- UHH!
- IF INUYASHA...
- DON'T YOU FAINT ON ME,
YOU STUPID GIRL.
- UHH.
[GRUNT]
UHH.
[RUMBLING]
- HUH?
- INUYASHA, LOOK OUT!
- HUH? AAH!
UHH! AAH!
UHH.
YOU AGAIN.
- YOU FORGET I'M IMMORTAL.
UHH!
[GASP]
IT'S HERE!
THIS RED SKULL!
THE HAIRS ARE CONNECTED
TO HER HAND!
- STOP THAT!
I'LL KILL YOU?
[GASP]
UHH!
AHH...
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
HUH?
- SO THAT'S WHAT
YURA REALLY WAS.
- YURA WAS A COMB?
- SURE.
WITH ALL THAT YOU'VE SEEN
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN HERE,
ARE YOU SURPRISED?
IT'S PROBABLY GOT POWERS,
' CAUSE IT WAS ONCE USED
TO COMB THE HAIR
OF THE DEAD.
YURA DIDN'T REALLY USE IT
SO MUCH AS IT USED HER.
UHH!
- INUYASHA, THAT STAB
IN YOUR CHEST.
IT ONLY HAPPENED BECAUSE
I'VE GOT YOUR KIMONO.
- IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE SACRED JEWEL?
- IT'S HERE.
I WONDER HOW LONG IT'LL TAKE
TO FIND THE REST OF IT.
- KAGOME, LET'S GO.
- HUH?
- WHAT?
- YOU NEVER SAID MY NAME BEFORE.
- YEAH? WHAT OF IT?
- IT'S JUST THAT I THINK
YOU LIKE ME MORE NOW, IS ALL.
- PFFFT.
DON'T GET EXCITED.
I STILL THINK
YOU'RE PRETTY USELESS.
- REMIND ME NEXT TIME
NOT TO SAVE YOU.
- AAH!
- UHH!
- IF IT HURTS SO MUCH,
YOU SHOULD'VE SAID SOMETHING.
- UHH.
LEAVE ME ALONE!
- INUYASHA, ONLY BY
WORKING TOGETHER
WILL YE TRIUMPH.
[COUGHS AND SNIFFLES]
ALSO, DON'T YE DARE FORGET
WHERE YE HAVE BURIED ME.
[AHCHOO]
[SNIFFLES]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- INUYASHA LOANED ME
PART OF HIS KIMONO,
AND BOY, DID IT COME IN HANDY.
GETTING BURNED
WOULD SO NOT BE COOL.
YOU KNOW, I THINK I READ
A STORY ONCE
ABOUT A MAGICAL KIMONO,
BUT WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT
IT WAS REAL?
ANYWAY, WHAT'S THIS SWORD
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
LOOKING FOR?
IF IT MEANS YOU HAVE TO FIGHT
YOUR OLDER BROTHER,
ARE YOU SURE IT'S WORTH IT?
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.