>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSAIGA.
>> KIKYO WAS RESURRECTED INTO A
BODY MADE OF BONES AND EARTH AND
CONTINUES TO EXIST THROUGH THE
SOULS OF THE DEAD.
EVEN NOW, THE BOND BETWEEN HER
AND INUYASHA REMAINS STRONG.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FUTILE FAIRY TALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> HUH?
>> HELP!
SOMEONE HELP ME!
>> A YOUNG CHILD SO LATE AT
NIGHT.
[CRYING]
>> YOU!
HUH.
OH, NO.
>> SIT!
[RUMBLING]
>> HUH?
>> WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR,
KAGOME?
>> SIT!
>> YAH!
>> SIT, SIT, SIT, SIT!
[GROANING]
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA, YOU'RE SUCH A JERK!
HMPH!
>> WAIT, KAGOME.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> FOR A WALK ALONE.
[LAUGHING]
>> KAGOME'S SCARY...
BUT HE DID KIND OF DESERVE IT.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT GUY!
I COOKED IT ESPECIALLY FOR HIM
AND MADE IT EXTRA SWEET, TOO,
JUST SO HE COULD EAT IT.
WHAT A SELFISH, UNGRATEFUL
CREEP!
HONESTLY, THAT'S THE LAST TIME I
EVER COOK ANYTHING FOR HIM.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE I WAS A BIT
HARSH, THOUGH.
HUH?
I SENSE A SACRED JEWEL SHARD
NEARBY.
I'M POSITIVE.
IT'S VERY FAINT, BUT IT'S
DEFINITELY A SHARD OF THE JEWEL.
>> WHAT THE HECK IS KAGOME'S
PROBLEM ANYWAY?
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOU'RE THE ONE WITH THE PROBLEM,
INUYASHA.
>> HOW SO?
ALL I DID WAS TELL THE TRUTH.
SINCE WHEN IS THAT A BAD THING?
>> OH, SO MUCH TO LEARN.
>> KAGOME COOKED THIS ESPECIALLY
FOR YOU!
HOW COULD YOU GO AN INSULT HER
LIKE THAT?
>> OH, YEAH?
WERE YOU GUYS ABLE TO EAT THAT
STUFF?
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
>> DISTINCT, YET PLEASING TO THE
PALATE.
>> THERE IS SOMETHING WRONG WITH
YOU PEOPLE.
HOW COULD YOU EAT STUFF SO SPICY
IT MAKES YOUR TONGUE BURN?
>> IT'S COMING FROM IN HERE.
THE SHARD SEEMS PURE ENOUGH.
>> HELP!
SOMEONE HELP!
HELP ME!
>> I BETTER CHECK IT OUT AND SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON.
[GASPING]
KIKYO.
[PANTING]
KIKYO HAS THE SHARD OF THE
SACRED JEWEL.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS SENSING.
>> IT SEEMS THAT YOU ALSO
POSSESS THE POWER OF A
PRIESTESS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
ARE YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
[PANTING]
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
ARE YOU SICK?
WHERE ARE YOUR SOUL COLLECTORS?
I DON'T SEEM THEM IN HERE.
WHY ARE YOU COLLAPSED IN HERE
LIKE THIS?
>> YOU CERTAINLY ASK A LOT OF
QUESTIONS, YOUNG LADY.
[CRIES, PANTING]
>> COME ON.
WE'D BETTER GET OUT OF HERE.
>> IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
WE'RE IN THE BELLY OF THE
PRIESTESS SEALER.
>> HUH?
PRIESTESS SEALER?
>> A DEMON WHO TRAPS PRIESTESSES
AND ABSORBS THEIR POWERS.
IT PUTS UP A BARRIER ON THE
OUTSIDE AND ALLOWS NO ONE BUT
PRIESTESSES INSIDE.
>> SO, WE'RE INSIDE THE DEMON'S
BELLY?
>> A PRIESTESS'S POWERS HAVE NO
EFFECT IN HERE.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO ESCAPE.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
IT LOOKS LIKE JUST AN ORDINARY
CAVE.
>> IT'S USELESS TO TRY ANYTHING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GONNA DIE IN
A PLACE LIKE THIS.
LET'S GET GOING.
SO, WHICH WAY DO YOU THINK'S THE
EXIT?
[SIGHS]
[HUMMING]
>> HE'S IN A BAD MOOD.
>> WHY DOESN'T HE JUST GO AND
SAY HE'S SORRY.
>> SHUT UP!
I'LL BURN IN HELL BEFORE I
APOLOGIZE TO HER!
HMM!
>> WHAT IS THIS GIRL TRYING TO
DO?
>> OH, BROTHER.
HOW DID I GET MYSELF INTO MY
MESS?
HMM?
[LAUGHING]
ON TOP OF THAT, WHY DID I HAVE
TO GET STUCK WITH KIKYO?
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
REALLY; JUST FINE.
>> HMM?
>> I WAS TALKING ABOUT INUYASHA,
NOT ABOUT MYSELF.
HE'S ALWAYS SAYING THINGS TO
MAKE PEOPLE MAD, BUT HE'S
GETTING A LOT BETTER, ACTUALLY.
I HAD A FIGHT WITH HIM JUST
BEFORE I CAME HERE.
I GUESS THINGS LIKE THAT NEVER
HAPPENED WITH YOU TWO.
WHAT AM I SAYING?
OF COURSE YOU DIDN'T!
[LAUGHING]
STUPID!
WHAT AM I BABBLING ABOUT?
WHY DO I HAVE TO SAY THINGS LIKE
THAT TO KIKYO OF ALL PEOPLE?
A LONG TIME AGO, SHE AND
INUYASHA WERE...
AAH!
HEY!
>> INUYASHA, HOLD ME.
>> I'LL DESTROY NARAKU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
I'LL PROTECT YOU.
>> INUYASHA...
>> KIKYO...
>> OH, IT DOESN'T GET MUCH WORSE
THAN THIS.
[COUGHING]
WHAT? KIKYO, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
[COUGHS]
WHY DID WE GET TRAPPED IN THIS
CAVE TOGETHER, I WONDER?
>> YOU'RE QUITE AN INCREDIBLE
WOMAN.
NORMALLY, A PRIESTESS WOULD BE
UNABLE TO EVEN MOVE INSIDE THIS
PLACE.
>> MEANING I'M NOT NORMAL?
>> LEAVE ME BEHIND.
I AM ALREADY DEAD, REMEMBER?
YOU HAVE A MUCH BETTER CHANCE OF
LIVING BY GOING ON ALONE RATHER
THAN BEING BURDENED BY ME.
IN ORDER TO ESCAPE FROM HERE,
YOU MUST DESTROY THE HEART,
WHICH YOU'LL FIND DEEPER IN THE
CAVE.
>> BUT I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> HUH?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT OUR CHANCES
ARE, BUT I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU
ORDER ME AROUND!
LISTEN, I'M NOT GIVING UP ON
YOU.
NOW, I NEED YOU TO STOP GIVING
UP ON THE THOUGHT OF ESCAPING
FROM HERE.
>> YOU'RE SERIOUS?
>> HUH?
I CAN HEAR SOMETHING.
[BUZZING GETTING LOUDER]
[GROANING]
>> KAGOME'S SURE TAKING HER
SWEET TIME.
WONDER IF SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
>> WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE SOMETHING HAPPENED TO HER.
>> I DON'T CLAIM TO BE AN
EXPERT, BUT DON'T YOU THINK YOU
SHOULD BRING HER BACK, INUYASHA?
>> SHUT UP!
WHO'D GO AFTER THAT--THAT--ARGH!
>> DON'T BE SO STUBBORN.
>> SANGO'S RIGHT.
IN THIS WORLD, YOU MUST LEARN TO
ACCEPT THINGS WITH GRACE AND
BE HONEST WITH YOURSELF--
TRUE TO YOUR FEELINGS.
>> KEEP IN MIND THAT THERE'S A
TIME AND PLACE FOR A LITTLE
RESTRAINT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
UGH!
>> HMM.
[BUZZING NOISE CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
[LAUGHS]
>> DON'T WORRY.
THAT WAS JUST A PRACTICE SHOT.
TAKE THAT.
AND THAT.
[GASPS]
[GROANING]
KIKYO, YOU SAVED ME!
[PANTING]
[BUZZING AGAIN]
KIKYO?
HMM?
THEY WON'T GET ME.
I'M NOT GONNA DIE IN HERE.
>> HRUMPH!
HMM.
>> HUH?
>> LISTEN UP.
I AM NOT GOING TO LOOK FOR
KAGOME.
I'M GOING FOR A WALK TO CLEAR MY
HEAD, AND THAT'S ALL.
[GIGGLING]
[GROANING]
>> THE LAST OF THE SOULS WITHIN
ME IS ABOUT TO FADE.
>> WE HAVE TO HURRY.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
WE'VE GOT TO SPEED UP IF WE'RE
GONNA MAKE IT OUT OF HERE.
[PANTING]
>> WHAT'S WITH THIS GIRL?
SHE'S SO WARM.
I CAN FEEL HER BLOOD MOVING
THROUGH HER.
WHY IS KAGOME SO STRONG?
INUYASHA MUST BE VERY WORRIED.
>> HUH?
I SERIOUSLY DOUBT IT.
WE JUST HAD AN ARGUMENT, SO HE'S
PROBABLY STILL FUMING OVER THAT,
AND BESIDES, HE COULDN'T
POSSIBLY KNOW WE'RE IN SO MUCH
TROUBLE.
IF WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT OUT OF
HERE, WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO IT
ON OUR OWN WITHOUT ANY HELP FROM
HIM.
KIKYO, HOLD ON JUST A BIT
LONGER.
>> KAGOME?
KAGOME?
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> THE CENTRAL CORE OF THE CAVE.
>> YOU MEAN...
[RUMBLING]
WHAT'S THAT?
>> IT'S COMING.
IF YOU DESTROY THE HEART OF THE
DEMON, THE CAVE WILL OPEN UP
AGAIN.
>> THAT'S THE HEART?
[GROANS]
OK, THEN THERE'S NO TIME TO
WASTE.
LET'S DESTROY IT AND GET OUT OF
HERE!
>> IT'S TOO MUCH FOR HER.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I TOLD YOU BEFORE.
A PRIESTESS'S POWER AND HER
ARROWS ARE COMPLETELY USELESS
AGAINST THIS DEMON.
>> NO WAY!
WHAT IS THAT DISGUSTING THING?
>> RUN, KAGOME.
RUN!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS TO STAY HERE.
[THUMPING]
>> OUR WAY OUT!
>> RUN NOW.
YOU'LL ONLY DIE IF YOU'RE
TRAPPED IN HERE.
>> FORGET IT!
I WON'T LEAVE YOU BEHIND!
[PANTING]
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME?
>> AAGH!
THERE MUST BE A WAY OUT OF HERE.
THERE MUST BE.
MY ARROWS ARE USELESS AGAINST
IT.
I'LL HAVE TO THINK OF SOMETHING
ELSE.
I KNOW.
IF I SHOOT THESE INTO THE
HEART...
AGH!
THE SHARDS!
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO GET THE
SHARDS BACK NOW.
[PANTING]
>> I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO GET THE
SHARDS BACK NOW.
[PANTING]
I'LL GIVE IT BACK.
GOT A PRESENT FOR YOU!
YES!
HUH?
WHAT?
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD DIDN'T
WORK.
>> THE SHARDS.
GIVE ME THE REMAINING SHARDS.
>> BUT...
>> HURRY!
>> ALL RIGHT THEN.
KIKYO.
HERE THEY ARE.
>> GIVE ME YOUR OTHER HAND.
>> HUH?
>> START PRAYING.
>> BUT WHAT SHOULD I PRAY FOR?
>> PLEASE TRUST ME.
JUST PRAY.
>> SURE.
ALL RIGHT.
THE SHARDS HAVE BECOME ONE.
I GET IT.
A SINGLE SHARD MIGHT
NOT BE ENOUGH TO DEFEAT THE
DEMON, BUT 3 SHARDS COMBINED IS.
>> THERE'S...ONLY...ONE...
CHANCE.
>> YOU'RE DEAD!
>> HUH?
[SIGHS]
UM, KIKYO?
>> YOU'RE STILL HERE?
YOU SHOULD BE ON YOUR WAY.
>> MM.
>> WAIT A MOMENT.
TELL ME WHY DIDN'T YOU GIVE UP
ON ME, KAGOME?
WHEN YOU WERE PRAYING, DID YOU
TRUST IN ME?
>> WHAT'S THE DEAL?
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU THIS
TALKATIVE BEFORE.
I CAN'T ANSWER YOUR QUESTION
BECAUSE I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT
MYSELF.
>> THEN WHY DID YOU SAVE ME?
A DEAD PERSON.
>> BECAUSE A CERTAIN GUY WE BOTH
KNOW WOULD BE HEARTBROKEN IF
YOU WEREN'T AROUND.
>> SAME FOR YOU.
>> HMM?
INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
>> YOU...CAME TO LOOK FOR ME?
>> UH...COME ON.
LET'S GET GOING.
>> HMM?
LISTEN, INUYASHA?
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> KAGOME, DO YOU KNOW
SESSHOMARU?
>> SURE, HE'S UNBELIEVABLY
STRONG.
AND SESSHOMARU IS COLD-HEARTED,
AND HE'S INUYASHA'S OLDER
BROTHER WHOM INUYASHA DOESN'T
GET ALONG WITH.
>> HOW SO?
>> WHEN INUYASHA AND KOGA FIGHT,
THEY'D NEVER CARRY IT TO THE
DEATH.
BUT SESSHOMARU WOULDN'T HESITATE
TO SLAY AN ENEMY.
>> NEXT TIME, SESSHOMARU AND
KOGA: A DANGEROUS ENCOUNTER.
>> THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
>> KOGA'S GONNA GET HIMSELF
KILLED.