>> UH! UH...
>> I'M GOING TO LOOK
INTO YOUR SOUL, OLD MAN.
>> HUH?
>> IS THAT IT?
>> ENTEI.
[SHOUTS]
>> YOUR WELCOME'S WEARING THIN!
>> WHAT THE HELL
DO I DO WITH THIS ONE?
IT'S NOT EVEN BREATHING.
UH! MAYBE IT IS ALIVE.
SO, ARE YOU BACK FROM THE DEAD?
[HEART BEATING SLOWLY]
HE'S DEFINITELY ALIVE.
[LOUD HEARTBEAT]
HE'S...
UH!
WHO ARE YOU?
>> IT'S SO FAST.
WE'LL NEVER CATCH UP.
>> DAMN IT.
>> IT'S NO USE.
HE'S GETTING AWAY.
>> HE'S GOING TO LAND.
>> ENTEI'S MASTER
MUST BE NEARBY.
WHY ELSE WOULD HE BE
GOING DOWN THERE?
>> YOU MEAN THE MAN-EATING DEMON
THAT'S SEALED UP THERE?
I'LL DESTROY THEM BOTH--
ENTEI AND HIM.
>> [GRUNTING]
THE MONK IS DEAD?
HA HA HA.
THAT'S SWEET, ENTEI,
COMING TO GREET YOUR OLD MASTER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE RAISE HELL
LIKE WE USED TO?
>> THAT AIN'T HAPPENING.
YOU MUST BE RYGOKOKI.
>> WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
>> NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
NOW SHUT UP AND CRAWL
BACK IN YOUR GRAVE.
>> YOU UNDERESTIMATE ME.
I'M THE GREAT RYGOKOKI,
THE ONLY RIDER ENTEI ALLOWS,
AND YOU'VE GOT GUTS,
PICKING A FIGHT WITH ME. GRR!
>> AH!
WHY, YOU...
>> TAKE THIS!
OOH!
>> AH! DAMN YOU!
>> HA HA HA. WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> YOU ALMOST HAD HIM THAT TIME.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE IT WON'T BE
SO EASY TO TAKE DOWN
THAT DEMON HORSE ENTEI.
>> HA HA HA!
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
HUMAN ATTACKS ARE USELESS.
I AM DESTINED
TO CONQUER THE WORLD.
>> WHATEVER.
>> HUH?
>> WIND STAR!
>> HE DODGED IT AGAIN.
>> DEALING WITH HIS SPEED
IS GOING TO BE TROUBLESOME.
>> DAMN. I'M COMING FOR YOU
ONE MORE TIME!
>> GET GOING, ENTEI.
>> HUH? OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
>> IT'S HUNGER. THAT'S WHY
I DON'T HAVE MY USUAL STRENGTH.
OTHERWISE, I WOULD NEVER LOSE
TO A WEAKLING LIKE HIM.
>> [SNIFFING]
DAMN IT.
>> INUYASHA! WHERE ARE
RYGOKOKI AND ENTEI?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THEY GOT AWAY ON ME.
>> WE HAVE TO FIND THEM,
AND WE'VE GOT TO HURRY
BEFORE SOMEONE ELSE GETS HURT.
>> RYGOKOKI IS
A MAN-EATING DEMON.
>> MIROKU'S RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND THEM FAST.
>> FOR STARTERS, LET'S HEAD OFF
THE SAME WAY THEY WENT.
I CAN TRACK THEIR SCENT
AS SOON AS WE GET CLOSE.
GET ON.
>> RIGHT.
>> LET'S GO. UH!
>> "BRING ME NEW CLOTHES,"
HE SAYS.
THE SECOND HE WAKES UP, THE KID
STARTS ORDERING ME AROUND AGAIN.
UH!
THAT'S STRANGE.
I WONDER WHAT COULD HAVE
HAPPENED TO THIS PLACE.
HUH?
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
>> WHAT KIND OF DEMON ARE YOU,
AND WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
>> WELL, I'M WARNING YOU.
STAY AWAY FROM THE HUMANS.
THEY'RE MINE.
>> SURE. WHATEVER.
>> HOLD ON.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> I WANT YOU TO BE MY WIFE.
>> WHAT?
>> IN TIME, I'M GOING TO
RULE THE WORLD,
AND YOU'LL BE MY WIFE.
NOT A BAD DEAL, IS IT?
>> YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE YOU CAN
CONQUER THE WORLD TO ME.
>> WHAT DID YOU--
>> FAREWELL.
>> INSULTING WENCH!
>> [NEIGHS]
>> WHAT?
>> ENTEI, LET'S GIVE HER
A TASTE OF MY POWER.
>> HE'S BECOMING TIRESOME.
DANCE OF BLADES!
DAMN THAT HORSE.
>> WOMAN, COME BACK HERE!
>> NOW HE'S GETTING IRRITATING.
SET DOWN. I'LL TAKE YOU ON
IF YOU WANT.
>> HA HA HA! I'LL PUT THIS
BEHIND US IF YOU APOLOGIZE
AND ASK ME TO TAKE YOU
FOR A WIFE.
>> HA. STOP DREAMING
AND START REGRETTING THAT
YOU EVER PICKED A FIGHT WITH ME.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
I'LL PROVE YOU WRONG.
EVEN ENTEI KNOWS
HOW TRULY POWERFUL I AM.
>> LIKE I SAID, YOU DON'T
LOOK VERY STRONG TO ME.
>> KAGURA, I'LL HANDLE HIM.
[ENTEI NEIGHS]
>> WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
>> IS THAT ALL YOU'VE GOT?
>> HOW DARE YOU, INSOLENT BRAT?!
WHAT'S WRONG, ENTEI?
[ENTEI NEIGHS]
WHAT IS IT, ENTEI?
>> GO.
>> ENTEI, WHAT'S
THE MATTER WITH YOU?
I'M YOUR MASTER.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
>> I THINK HE HAS FORGOTTEN.
>> SHUT UP! HE'S THE ONE
THAT DECIDES WHO'S MOST FITTING
TO RIDE ON HIS BACK, AND I AM
THE MASTER THAT HE CHOSE.
I'M THE VICTOR.
HA HA HA HA. BEHOLD!
I AM THE RIDER OF ENTEI!
ONWARD, ENTEI!
ENTEI, WHAT CAN YOU POSSIBLY
SEE IN THIS CHILD?
WATCH THIS.
>> HA HA HA.
>> THE KID.
>> YAH!
HUH? WHERE'D HE GO?
>> OVER HERE.
>> WHY, YOU LITTLE RAT.
DAMN YOU. ENOUGH!
AAH!
AM I GOING TO DIE?
SLAIN BY A MERE CHILD.
NO! AH...
>> NOT TOO BAD.
>> ISN'T IT A LITTLE
BIG FOR YOU?
>> SAVE YOUR WISECRACKS.
I HAVE TO FOCUS ON GETTING USED
TO MY NEW BODY.
>> THIS KID'S DIFFERENT
FROM NARAKU.
HE DOESN'T MIND
GETTING HIS HANDS DIRTY.
>> NOW, THEN...
>> LOOKS LIKE EVERYONE
WHO LIVED HERE WAS KILLED
IN THE ATTACK.
>> DO YOU THINK
RYGOKOKI DID THIS?
>> COME HERE! LOOK AT THIS!
>> A HORSE'S HOOF MARK.
>> IT'S ENORMOUS.
>> WE'D BETTER FIND THEM
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
>> ENTEI'S HOOFPRINTS
COME FROM THAT DIRECTION, BUT
THEY COME TO A STOP RIGHT HERE.
>> THEN THIS IS WHERE HE
MUST HAVE TAKEN OFF FROM.
>> SO HE PROBABLY FLEW OFF
IN THIS DIRECTION.
>> HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
>> IS SOMETHING WRONG?
>> I KNOW THIS SCENT.
>> STAY ON YOUR TOES, EVERYONE.
AN AURA, DEMONIC AURA,
IS HEADED THIS WAY.
>> AAH!
>> IT'S ENTEI! HUH!
>> YOU GOT GUTS COMING TO ME.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT MUCH.
WIND STAR!
>> IT'S GOING TO HIT HIM
THIS TIME!
>> A BARRIER?
>> HUH?
>> HA HA HA.
THAT'S SOME GREETING, INUYASHA.
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT'S NOT RYGOKOKI.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT. IT'S NOT HIM.
I KILLED RYGOKOKI.
>> WHO IS HE?
>> IT SEEMS ENTEI HERE
HAS CHOSEN ME AS HIS MASTER
AFTER WITNESSING MY STRENGTH.
>> IT'S A KID.
>> HE'S JUST A CHILD.
>> OR MAYBE HE CHOSE ME
FOR RELEASING HIM FROM THE SEAL.
>> YOU MEAN YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SET THIS DEMON HORSE FREE?
>> THAT CAN'T BE.
IT WAS KAGURA AND THE INFANT
WHO BROKE THE SEAL.
>> AND THE INFANT
WAS SPLIT IN TWO
BY THE MONK'S SPIRITUAL POWER.
HE COULDN'T HAVE LIVED.
>> HA. YOU ARE SO NAIVE.
THE SPIRITUAL POWERS OF A HUMAN
MONK COULDN'T KILL ME.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
DOES THAT MEAN YOU'RE THAT BABY?
>> I AM HAKUDOSHI.
AS YOU'VE GUESSED,
I'M NARAKU'S INCARNATION.
>> HAKUDOSHI?
>> SO YOU ARE ONE
OF NARAKU'S CREATIONS.
>> HAKUDOSHI, I'VE HEARD
THAT YOU'VE KILLED MANY MONKS
AND PRIESTS IN YOUR SEARCH
OF THE BORDER BETWEEN
THIS WORLD AND THE NEXT.
WHAT'S THERE?
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
>> HA HA HA. I WILL SEARCH
FOR THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
WOULD YOU CARE TO JOIN ME?
>> YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR THE JEWEL SHARD?
>> WATCH WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING, KID.
YOU'RE GIVING AWAY TOO MUCH.
>> THERE'S NO NEED TO HIDE IT.
>> THERE ISN'T?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> AS THE SAYING GOES,
THE MORE, THE MERRIER.
YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL THAT I'VE
GIVEN YOU THAT LITTLE LEAD.
>> HE SEEMS TO BE TELLING
THE TRUTH ABOUT THE SHARD.
THAT MUCH IS CERTAIN.
>> I DON'T GIVE A DAMN ABOUT
THE NEXT WORLD OR WHATEVER,
BUT IF THERE'S A SHARD
TO BE FOUND THERE,
THEN GO FIND IT YOURSELF! YAH!
DAMN IT.
>> HE GOT AWAY.
>> I WON'T LET THEM ESCAPE.
I'LL FIND THEM. YOU JUST WATCH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO NOW?
KILL ANOTHER MONK OR PRIEST?
>> I'M DONE WITH THEM.
HUMANS AREN'T STRONG ENOUGH
FOR ME NOW.
I LOOKED INSIDE THE MONK'S SOUL
BEFORE HE SPLIT ME IN TWO.
WAS THAT THE BORDER I SAW
BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT?
IT WAS A WORLD OF WHITE MISTS.
I NEED TO LEARN MORE
ABOUT THE PLACE, WHICH MEANS...
I NEED DEMONS.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> FIND ME SOME DEMONS
THAT APPEAR TO BE STRONG.
>> HUH? DEMONS?
>> AND SO YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED
ANYTHING IN THIS AREA EITHER?
>> NO. AS YOU CAN SEE,
IT'S VERY PEACEFUL HERE.
>> NO DEMON HORSE
RIDDEN BY A YOUNG CHILD?
>> AFRAID I HAVEN'T SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I'M SORRY I HAVEN'T
BEEN MUCH HELP.
>> OH, NO. THANK YOU
FOR YOUR TIME.
>> SO FAR, WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO COME UP WITH A SINGLE CLUE.
>> IT'S ODD, THOUGH.
EVER SINCE HAKUDOSHI ESCAPED
FROM US, THERE HASN'T BEEN
ANY WORD OF NEW ATTACKS ON
SHRINEKEEPERS AND TEMPLE MONKS.
>> YES. EXCEPT NOW I KEEP
SENSING STRANGE DEMONIC AURAS...
AND MORE THAN JUST ONE.
>> STRANGE DEMONIC AURAS?
>> BY THEMSELVES, THEY HARDLY
SEEM WORTH NOTICING.
WHAT WORRIES ME MORE
IS THEIR WILD MOVEMENTS.
>> YOU MEAN THEY DON'T SEEM
TO BE HEADED ANYWHERE?
>> RIGHT. IT'S MORE LIKE THEY'RE
DRIFTING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> NOTHING SMELLS BETTER
THAN FRESH GRILLED FISH.
[COUGHING]
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, SHIPPO?
>> SURE. I'M FINE.
SHOULDN'T MIROKU AND SANGO
BE GETTING BACK HERE SOON?
>> YEAH.
>> I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT NARAKU'S INCARNATION
HAKUDOSHI WOULD COME OUT
AND TELL US THE LOCATION
OF THE LAST JEWEL SHARD.
>> MM-HMM. OTHER THAN THAT ONE,
THE ONLY ONES LEFT
ARE KOHAKU'S
AND THE ONES IN KOGA'S LEGS.
NARAKU HAS THE REST OF
THE JEWEL SHARDS, UNFORTUNATELY.
WE'VE GOT TO DO WHATEVER IT
TAKES TO PREVENT NARAKU
FROM GETTING ANY MORE SHARDS.
>> THAT INUYASHA. I WONDER
WHERE HE WENT TO ANYWAY.
>> KNOWING HIM, HE PROBABLY
COULDN'T SIT STILL.
>> DAMN IT. I CAN'T PICK UP
ANY SCENT OF HAKUDOSHI,
AND I DON'T GET THIS THING
ABOUT THE BORDER BETWEEN
THIS WORLD AND THE NEXT.
ISN'T THERE SOME KIND OF CLUE?
ANYTHING AT ALL? HUH?
WHAT IS THAT?
>> [BLOWING]
THIS LOOKS DELICIOUS.
HUH?
>> INUYASHA?
>> [ROARING]
>> AAH!
>> WHAT THE HECK IS THAT THING?
>> RUN, KAGOME!
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME!
>> INUYASHA!
[SHOUTS]
KAGOME, ARE YOU TWO ALL RIGHT?
>> WHERE WERE YOU, YOU IDIOT?!
YOU'RE JUST LUCKY I WAS HERE
TO PROTECT KAGOME!
>> HEY, I'M SORRY
I LEFT YOU, KAGOME.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT. HEY.
LOOK AT IT.
WHAT'S WITH THIS DEMON?
>> KAGOME.
>> SANGO. MIROKU.
>> DID YOU DO THIS, INUYASHA?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU SURE GOT CARRIED AWAY.
>> WHAT THE HECK IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
>> YOU SLICED THE DEMON'S
HEAD RIGHT OFF.
>> INUYASHA DIDN'T DO THAT.
IT WAS HEADLESS FROM THE START.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE SURE IT DIDN'T HAVE
A HEAD WHEN IT FIRST ATTACKED?
>> DEFINITELY. THAT'S WHAT
MADE IT EXTRA SCARY.
>> DOES THIS HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THOSE DRIFTING
DEMONIC AURAS?
>> YES. IT WAS PROBABLY
CREATING ONE OF THE AURAS.
>> IF YOU ASK ME, IT LOOKS
LIKE HE WAS ATTACKED
WITH SOME KIND OF BLADE.
>> BY A BLADE?
THEN DO YOU THINK SOMEBODY
LOPPED ITS HEAD OFF?
>> YEAH, BUT DEMONS ARE
PRETTY TOUGH TO KILL, THOUGH.
THAT'S WHY THE BODY
WAS MOVING BY ITSELF.
>> THEN THE OTHER DEMONIC AURAS.
>> PERHAPS. BUT WHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
BUT TAKE A LOOK AT THAT CUT.
WHOEVER TOOK THIS DEMON'S HEAD
WAS A TERRIBLE SWORDSMAN.
>> YOU CAN TELL THAT
FROM THE CUT?
>> YEAH.
>> HA HA HA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, BOY?
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF THIS,
TRESPASSING ON MY TERRITORY?
CURSE YOU.
>> WHAT IS THIS BRAT
PLANNING ANYWAY?
>> LET'S GO.
>> I'M KANTA.
AS YOU CAN SEE, I'M A--
>> RACCOON DOG?
>> RIVER OTTER.
KANTA'S FATHER HAS BEEN
BEHEADED BY HAKUDOSHI.
>> IF WE CAN FIND HIS BODY,
WE MAY BE ABLE TO SAVE HIM.
>> ISN'T IT IMPOSSIBLE
TO BRING HIM BACK TO LIFE
IF HIS HEAD HAS BEEN CUT OFF?
>> HURRY, INUYASHA.
WE MIGHT STILL BE IN TIME.
>> YEAH, EXCEPT WE'VE GOT TO
GET PAST THE CREEP
NEAR KANTA'S FATHER.
>> NEXT TIME, 3,000 LEAGUES
IN SEARCH OF FATHER.
>> IS IT TELLING ME TO SAVE IT?