>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSAIGA.
>> THANKS TO MYOGA, WE NARROWLY
ESCAPED BEING KILLED BY
MUKOTSU'S POISON.
NOW WE'RE FOLLOWING A NEW LEAD
TOWARD A SCARED JEWEL SHARD.
WHAT?
WHY IS KIKYO HERE?
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE, "INUYASHA."
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> TO LIVE IS TO DIE.
TO DIE IS TO LIVE.
MY NAME IS KIKYO.
I'M A PRIESTESS WHO'S UNABLE TO
LEAVE THIS WORLD AND REACH THE
SACRED PLACE.
NO, THAT IS NOT ENTIRELY THE
TRUTH.
ONCE I WAS A PRIESTESS.
NOW I AM BUT A CORPSE WITH A
CURSED, FALSE EXISTENCE.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH I DESIRE TO
DO GOOD AND HELP OTHERS, THE
TRUTH IS, I LIVE OFF THE SOULS
OF THE DEAD.
PURE IS IMPURE.
IMPURE IS PURE.
GOOD IS EVIL.
EVIL IS GOOD.
OR IS IT?
IN THE HEARTS OF MEN LIES BOTH
GOOD AND EVIL.
THE TWO COEXIST.
SOME MEN BECOME GOOD, AND OTHERS
BECOME EVIL.
IT IS THE WAY OF THIS WORLD.
HOWEVER, I AM MOST INTRIGUED BY
THAT PHYSICIAN WHO CALLS HIMSELF
SUIKOTSU.
HE IS CERTAINLY ONE OF THE DEAD
LIKE MYSELF, AND YET HE LOOKS
AFTER ORPHAN CHILDREN AND GIVES
MEDICAL ATTENTION TO THE
VILLAGERS WITH A SINGULAR
UNSELFISHNESS.
IT WOULD SEEM THAT HE HANGS ON
TO LIFE THROUGH THE SHIKON JEWEL
SHARD IN HIS NECK, BUT
SURPRISINGLY, I CAN DETECT NO
TRACE OF CLOUDINESS IN ITS GLOW.
ONLY THE MOST GOOD-HEARTED AND
PURE OF SPIRIT COULD MAKE IT
THUS.
COULD THERE TRULY BE SUCH A
PERSON?
I THINK I SHALL STAY AND OBSERVE
THE SITUATION A WHILE LONGER.
>> [GRUNT]
INUYASHA?
>> HMM?
>> I'LL TAKE OVER THE WATCH.
EVEN YOU NEED TO GET A LITTLE
REST, TOO, YOU KNOW.
>> I DON'T NEED TO SLEEP.
>> COME ON.
YOU CAN'T STAY AWAKE FOREVER,
AND BESIDES, I DON'T THINK THE
BAND OF 7 IS GONNA ATTACK
ANYTIME SOON.
>> I SURE HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> ACCORDING TO KOGA, HE
DEFEATED THE ONE NAMED KYOKOTSU
OF THE BAND OF 7.
SESSHOMARU DEFEATED THE POISON
MASTER, MUKOTSU; AND YOU DEALT
WITH GINKOTSU, DIDN'T YOU,
INUYASHA?
>> [GROANING]
[SHOUTING]
>> NOW TRY THIS.
WIND SCAR!
>> AAARGH!
>> SO THAT MEANS THAT 3 OF THE 7
HAVE BEEN TAKEN CARE OF ALREADY.
THE REMAINING 4 ARE BOUND TO BE
A LOT MORE CAUTIOUS NOW.
>> YEAH, AND A LOT MORE
DANGEROUS.
SO BEFORE THE REMAINING 4
REGROUP AND ATTACK US, I PLAN TO
MAKE THE FIRST MOVE.
>> THE FIRST MOVE?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M GONNA GET THEM BEFORE THEY
CAN GET US.
>> I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN YOU WOULD
PLAN SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
>> THERE ARE LOTS OF WAYS TO
FIND THEM.
THEY REEK OF DEAD BODIES AND
GRAVEYARD SOIL, AND THOSE
BASTARDS POSSESS SHIKON JEWEL
SHARDS.
I WON'T REST UNTIL THEY'RE DEAD,
EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM.
>> OHH.
OHH.
I CAN SAVE THEM.
I KNOW I CAN SAVE THEM.
>> IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT CHILD.
JUST LET HER DIE!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
>> DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
THERE'S STILL HOPE.
>> BUT THE SAMURAI ARE HEADING
THIS WAY!
THEY'LL KILL US!
>> FLEE IF YOU WANT, BUT I'M
GOING TO SAVE THIS CHILD.
[GASP]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, FOOLISH
MAN?
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> WHY DON'T YOU DO US BOTH A
FAVOR AND STOP ACTING LIKE A
SAINT?
THE REAL YOU COULDN'T CARE LESS
ABOUT SAVING PEOPLE.
DEEP INSIDE, YOU WANT TO HURT
PEOPLE, TO KILL THEM.
ISN'T THAT SO?
HA HA HA!
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I--
>> HEY...
>> [GASP]
>> WE'VE COME FOR YOU.
>> MAN, QUIT BEING SO DIFFICULT,
WILL YOU?
>> [YELLING]
>> IDIOT!
WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU CAN GO?
[LAUGHTER]
>> AAH!
OHH...
IT WAS A DREAM.
OHH.
WHAT A HORRIBLE DREAM.
WAS IT...
>> YOU'RE AWAKE ALREADY, DR.
SUIKOTSU?
>> HUH?
OH!
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, LADY KIKYO.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> AHH.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING TO BE A
FINE DAY TODAY, DON'T YOU THINK?
>> I DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING THIS MAN VERY
CLOSELY, YET I'VE NOT FELT EVEN
THE SLIGHTEST PRESENCE OF EVIL
ABOUT HIM.
ALL I SEE IS THE FACE OF A
GOOD-HEARTED DOCTOR.
SO WHY HAS SUCH A MAN GROUNDED
HIS SPIRIT IN THIS WORLD?
>> [PANTING]
>> OVER THAT WAY!
I FEEL THE PRESENCE OF A SACRED
JEWEL SHARD!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT YOU NOW, YOU BASTARD.
>> FASTER, INUYASHA.
WHAT IS THIS BAND OF 7?
AND YOU'RE SAYING THAT THERE ARE
MORE OF THEM?
>> YEAH. WHAT ABOUT IT?
>> I SEE.
VERY BRAVE OF YOU.
CROW!
MASTER INUYASHA, I JUST
REMEMBERED SOME IMPORTANT
BUSINESS I REALLY MUST SEE TO.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME...
>> HEY! HOLD ON!
>> GIVE THEM HELL!
>> WHAT KIND OF BUSINESS DOES A
FLEA HAVE?
>> NEVER MIND, INUYASHA.
HE'S ALREADY DONE MORE THAN
ENOUGH.
IT'S BECAUSE OF MYOGA THAT THE 3
OF US ARE ALIVE TODAY.
>> HMM.
YOU'RE RIGHT, KAGOME.
>> JUST LET HIM GO.
>> HMM.
>> THANK YOU, MYOGA.
IS DR. SUIKOTSU AWAY?
>> YES.
HE WENT TO PICK HERBS.
>> OH, I SEE.
>> IF YOU LIKE, I CAN HELP YOU
INSTEAD.
>> REALLY?
OH, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> INUYASHA, THERE'S SOMETHING I
DON'T GET.
>> WHAT?
>> UNTIL NOW, THE JEWEL SHARDS
POSSESSED BY THE BAND OF 7 HAVE
BEEN TAINTED, BUT THIS ONE'S
VERY PURE.
>> WHAT, SO THEN IT DOESN'T
BELONG TO THE BAND OF 7?
>> I'M NOT SURE.
>> DR. SUIKOTSU, I FOUND SOME!
>> AH, GREEN GENTIAN.
GOOD FOR A WEAK STOMACH.
WE'LL PICK THESE, AND THEN WE'LL
GO HOME, OK?
>> UH-HUH.
HUH?
>> [WHIMPER]
>> WELL, WELL, WELL,
I FINALLY FOUND YOU.
>> HUH?
>> YES, OF COURSE I REMEMBER.
DR. SUIKOTSU CAME TO THIS
VILLAGE OF OURS SHORTLY AFTER
THE TOMB OF THE 7 BROKE APART.
>> DID YOU SAY THE BAND OF 7?
>> YES.
BY A STRANGE COINCIDENCE, DR.
SUIKOTSU HAD THE SAME NAME AS
ONE OF THOSE ACCURSED BEINGS.
SO THERE WAS A PANIC AMONGST THE
VILLAGERS, WHO BELIEVED HE WAS A
SPECTER WHO HAD ESCAPED FROM A
TOMB.
>> DR. SUIKOTSU IS A MEMBER OF
THE BAND OF 7?
>> OF COURSE NOT!
EVEN IF THE NAME IS THE SAME,
THEY HAVE OPPOSITE
PERSONALITIES.
I WITNESSED THE EXECUTION OF
THOSE 7 HEINOUS WARRIORS WITH MY
VERY OWN EYES.
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO, BUT I
REMEMBER IT CLEARLY.
IT WAS 15 YEARS AGO, TO BE
PRECISE.
7 MERCENARIES WHO CALLED
THEMSELVES THE BAND OF 7 ESCAPED
HERE FROM THE EASTERN LANDS.
THEY COMMITTED COUNTLESS
ATROCITIES, LEAVING DEATH AND
SUFFERING IN THEIR WAKE, BUT
THEN THEY FELL INTO A TRAP SET
BY THE LORD OF THE REGION AND
WERE EXECUTED BY THE LORD'S MEN.
SUIKOTSU, ONE OF THE 7
MERCENARIES, WAS A
TERRIFYING-LOOKING CREATURE WHO
RESEMBLED MORE DEMON THAN
HUMAN--TRULY EVIL BEING.
BUT OUR SUIKOTSU IS TOTALLY
DIFFERENT.
WHY, THE MAN IS ALMOST A SAINT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> HUH?
OH.
THAT FEELS SO MUCH BETTER NOW.
THE PAIN'S ALL GONE AWAY.
>> THERE ARE PLENTY OF MEDICINAL
HERBS GROWING IN THIS REGION
THAT I WAS ABLE TO USE.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, YOUNG
LADY.
PLEASE GIVE MY REGARDS TO
DR. SUIKOTSU.
IS THERE SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> I SENSE A JEWEL SHARD.
>> HUH?
IT'S APPROACHING.
TWO OF THEM--NO, 3.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH ME?
>> DROP THE ACT.
I KNOW YOU'RE ONE OF THE BAND OF
7.
>> HOLD ON.
THERE MUST BE SOME MISTAKE.
I'M A PHYSICIAN.
I'M NOT A WARRIOR OF ANY KIND.
>> DON'T TRY TO DENY IT.
YOUR BODY REEKS WITH THE SMELL
OF DEATH AND GRAVEYARD SOIL,
JUST LIKE THE REST OF YOUR
TWISTED BAND.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> WHAT'S THAT?
SMELL OF DEATH?
>> I'LL MAKE YOU SHOW YOUR TRUE
COLORS!
>> RUN, CHILDREN!
>> INUYASHA, WAIT A SECOND!
>> BE CAREFUL!
DON'T HURT THE CHILDREN!
>> I'M NOT STUPID, YOU KNOW.
>> AAH!
UNH! UNH!
>> DR. SUIKOTSU!
>> HUH?
WHY, YOU!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> OHH.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, DR.
SUIKOTSU?
>> ARE YOU HURT?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, YOU
TWO.
NOW, HURRY AND RUN AWAY FROM
HERE.
>> NO.
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
>> SHE'S RIGHT!
WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE YOU BEHIND.
>> [GRUNT]
>> HUH?
>> TO THOSE KIDS, YOU'RE LIKE
THE BAD GUY ATTACKING A GOOD GUY
FOR NO REASON.
I HATE TO SAY IT, BUT I THINK WE
MAY HAVE BEEN WRONG ABOUT HIM.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> HE'S NOTHING AT ALL LIKE THE
OTHER MEMBERS OF THE BAND OF 7
WE'VE ENCOUNTERED SO FAR.
>> HA! IT'S A PUT-ON.
IT'S THE SAME TRICK RENKOTSU
USED.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GOING TO BE
FOOLED A SECOND TIME.
NOW SHOW YOUR TRUE SELF, YOU
MAGGOT!
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> HUH?
>> THE VILLAGE!
IT'S BURNING!
>> OH, NO! THE VILLAGERS!
>> WAIT!
WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
I'M NOT FINISHED WITH YOU YET.
>> [SCREAMING]
>> GET AWAY, QUICKLY!
>> PLEASE COME WITH US.
DON'T STAY HERE.
>> DON'T WORRY.
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
MMM!
UNH.
[GASP]
>> HMM.
>> HUH.
>> HA HA HA!
>> THESE MEN ARE 3 MEMBERS OF
THE BAND OF 7.
>> LADY KIKYO!
>> HMM?
>> WHAT ON EARTH IS THIS?
>> SO THIS IS WHERE YOU'VE BEEN.
>> HUH?
>> HEY, SUIKOTSU.
>> GRR!
>> JEEZ, YOU SURE MADE IT
DIFFICULT FOR US TO FIND YOU.
>> OHH!
>> HUH?
>> COME ON, SUIKOTSU.
WE CAME ALL THIS WAY TO GET YOU,
DON'T YOU KNOW?
YOU SHOULD BE MORE GRATEFUL.
>> YES.
>> MMM.
>> [GASP]
[GASP]
OHH.
WHO ARE YOU?
WHO ARE YOU, AND WHAT COULD YOU
POSSIBLY WANT WITH ME?
>> HE REALLY ISN'T LYING.
THEN WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> [PANTING]
>> THIS IS TERRIBLE.
>> HOLES EVERYWHERE!
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN BATTLEFIELDS
THAT LOOKED ANYTHING LIKE THIS
BEFORE.
>> THE BAND OF 7, NO DOUBT.
I SENSE A SACRED JEWEL SHARD
NEARBY.
>> OH, YEAH.
I'D KNOW THAT DISGUSTING SMELL
OF THEIRS ANYWHERE.
HUH?
[GASP]
KIKYO.
>> INUYASHA, I SEE YOU'VE COME
TO THE NORTHERN LANDS AS WELL.
>> LADY KIKYO!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> KIKYO.
WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
>> NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
>> OH, RIGHT, OF COURSE NOT.
>> YOU'RE ALL STILL ALIVE.
I MUST ADMIT I'M IMPRESSED.
>> YES.
>> HEY, INUYASHA!
>> HA!
THIS WORKS FOR ME PERFECTLY.
I CAN DEAL WITH YOU ALL AT ONCE.
>> TO THINK YOU WENT TO SUCH
GREAT PAINS JUST TO STAY ALIVE.
TOO BAD IT WAS ALL FOR NOTHING.
>> WELL, WE'LL JUST HAVE TO SEE
ABOUT THAT NOW, WON'T WE?
>> IF ONLY THEY DIDN'T POSSESS
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS, I COULD
SUCK THEM INTO MY WIND TUNNEL
IN AN INSTANT.
>> EVERYONE JUST STAY BACK.
YOU'RE NOT FULLY RECOVERED YET,
SO YOU CAN'T HANDLE THEM.
LEAVE THESE LOWLIFES TO ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, JAKOTSU,
I WANT YOU TO DEAL WITH
SUIKOTSU.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
WHY ME?
>> BECAUSE I ASKED YOU, THAT'S
WHY.
>> OH!
THEY INTEND TO KILL ME.
>> I'LL DEAL WITH INUYASHA AND
HIS LITTLE FRIENDS.
>> OH, RENKOTSU, COME ON!
WHY ARE YOU BEING SO UNFAIR TO
ME?
YOU ALWAYS KEEP ME AWAY FROM MY
INUYASHA.
YOU KNOW, I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
THAT MAYBE YOU'VE TAKEN A LIKING
TO INUYASHA, TOO.
>> IF YOU KEEP TALKING SUCH
NONSENSE, I'LL PULL THAT TONGUE
OUT OF YOUR HEAD.
>> QUIT YOUR BABBLING, YOU
FOOLS.
I'LL TAKE YOU ALL ON RIGHT NOW.
>> HA HA HA!
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
>> OH, YEAH?
UNH!
HUH?
YOU ARE SUCH A PATHETIC FOOL,
RENKOTSU.
THESE FLAMES OF YOURS AREN'T
EVEN HOT!
>> MAYBE FOR YOU!
>> AAH!
>> NO! IT'S A NET OF FIRE!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> AAH!
>> HA HA HA!
WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO TELL YOU
WHAT YOUR WEAKNESS IS, INUYASHA?
YOUR NEED TO PROTECT THESE POOR,
PITIFUL HUMAN FRIENDS OF YOURS!
>> GO TO HELL!
>> YOU FIRST!
HA HA HA!
>> OH.
OHH.
NO, DON'T TRY AND RESIST,
SUIKOTSU.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO YOU OR YOUR
FRIENDS ARE, BUT YOU'VE COME
AFTER ME FOR SOME UNFATHOMABLE
REASON.
SO THEN KILL ME AND LEAVE
EVERYONE ELSE ALONE.
WHY ATTACK THE WHOLE VILLAGE?
>> [SIGH]
HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA KEEP THIS
UP, SUIKOTSU?
OH, HURRY UP AND SNAP OUT OF IT,
OK?
>> OHH.
>> OTHERWISE, I'LL KILL YOU FOR
REAL!
>> AAH!
>> HA HA!
>> GET BACK!
>> OHH!
OHH! OHH!
>> FIRE, GINKOTSU.
>> AAH!
UNH!
DAMN.
>> JAKOTSU, SHAME ON YOU.
>> GRR!
>> SHOOT THEM, GINKOTSU.
>> YES!
>> AAH!
UNH!
>> KIKYO!
>> INUYASHA, IF YOU DON'T PAY
CLOSER ATTENTION, YOUR FRIENDS
WILL DIE.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA.
>> [GROANING]
THE SOULS ARE LEAVING ME.
>> HUH?
LADY KIKYO, NO!
LADY KIKYO, HOLD ON.
>> HELP US!
>> DR. SUIKOTSU!
>> PLEASE!
>> LISTEN TO ME, CHILDREN!
STAY AWAY!
>> DR. SUIKOTSU!
>> HELP!
>> STAY BACK!
STAY AWAY FROM HERE!
HUH?
>> HMM?
>> DR. SUIKOTSU!
HELP US!
>> HUH?
>> PLEASE, NO!
[GASP]
>> [GASP]
>> HMM.
>> [MOANS]
>> AAH!
DR. SUIKOTSU!
>> WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
>> ISN'T HE PART OF THE BAND OF
7?
>> DR. SUIKOTSU.
>> I'M ALL RIGHT.
ARE EITHER OF YOU HURT?
>> NO.
>> WE'RE OK.
>> AHH.
HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> ♪ PURE HAS BECOME IMPURE
IMPURE HAS NOW BECOME PURE...♪
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, YOU FOOL?
QUIT ACTING LIKE A SAINT.
YOUR HEART CRAVES TO MURDER AND
KILL.
YOU KNOW IT TO BE TRUE.
>> HUH?
>> HIS SACRED JEWEL SHARD HAS
TURNED BLACK.
>> PURE IS IMPURE.
IMPURE IS PURE.
GOOD IS EVIL.
EVIL IS GOOD.
>> HUH?
DR. SUIKOTSU?
HUH!
AAH!
>> HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, DR.
SUIKOTSU?
>> GOOD.
HE'S AWAKE.
>> YES.
>> HE IS.
[CHUCKLING]
>> HA HA HA!
>> DOCTOR!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> SO I WAS RIGHT.
>> INUYASHA, YOU HAVE TO HURRY
AND SAVE HIM.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT!
>> HA HA HA!
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> AHH!
>> JUST WHAT ARE YOU?
>> HEH HEH HEH!
WHO, ME?
I'M SUIKOTSU OF THE BAND OF 7.
>> HMM?
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE'S A TOTALLY DIFFERENT PERSON
THAN HE WAS A MINUTE AGO.
>> DOES DR. SUIKOTSU HAVE TWO
SOULS CONTAINED IN THAT ONE
BODY?
>> WHATEVER!
JUST AS I THOUGHT, YOU'RE ONE OF
THE BAND OF 7 AFTER ALL!
>> HA!
THIS IS HOW YOU CONDUCT
CLOSE-QUARTERS COMBAT.
>> SUIKOTSU'S TRUE EVIL SELF IS
AWAKENED, AND HE BEGINS HIS
ASSAULT.
>> GINKOTSU BEARS HIS CLAWS
AGAINST KIKYO.
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA":
"HIDDEN IN THE MIST:
ONWARD TO MT. HAKUREI."
KIKYO REVEALS THE POWER OF THE
SACRED MOUNTAIN.