>> HERE WE COME!
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> THE BATTLE CONTINUES TO RAGE
AGAINST THE BAND OF SEVEN, WHO
ARE HELL-BENT ON AVENGING
GINKOTSU'S DEATH.
RENKOTSU TRIES TO STEAL THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS FROM THE
SERIOUSLY INJURED KOGA.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ALL RIGHT.
HMM.
[THINKING]
I SHOULD HAVE MOUNTED THIS ON
HIM, AS WELL.
>> I'VE HAD JUST ABOUT ENOUGH OF
YOU!
AAAH!
WHAT?
[GRUNTING]
>> DAMN IT.
I CAN'T MOVE.
[GRUNTING]
[THINKING]
WHAT SHOULD I DO WITH GINKOTSU'S
JEWEL SHARD?
IF I CARRY IT AROUND LIKE THIS,
BANKOTSU WILL JUST TAKE IT FROM
ME.
NO WAY I'M LETTING THAT HAPPEN.
THAT PUNK'S NOT GETTING IT FROM
ME.
[GROANING]
MY WOUND IS HEALING.
YOU CAN'T ACCOMPLISH ANYTHING
WHEN YOU'RE DEAD.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, GINKOTSU?
>> [BUZZING]
YOU FOUND HIM?
EXCELLENT.
NEVER MIND REPORTING TO
BANKOTSU.
THERE'S ONE MORE JOB I WANT YOU
TO DO.
>> [GROANING QUIETLY]
>> LOOK, HE'S AWAKE!
>> KOGA!
>> WHAT A RELIEF.
YOU WERE UNCONSCIOUS ALL NIGHT
LONG.
>> KAGOME.
>> KOGA, DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU?
>> YOU WERE CAUGHT IN THAT BLAST
WHEN THAT IRON MONSTER GINKOTSU
EXPLODED.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> OH, MAN.
[SNIFFING]
I STINK TO HIGH HEAVEN!
HOW COME?
[SNIFFING]
MY WHOLE BODY REEKS OF DOG!
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED.
INUYASHA CARRIED YOU HERE TO
HIDE YOU SOME PLACE SAFE.
>> WHAT?!
>> KAGOME WAS WORRIED, SO SHE
ASKED HIM TO DO IT.
>> WHY'D YOU LET THAT MUTT CARRY
ME FOR?!
YOU TWO SHOULD HAVE PACKED ME,
NOT INUYASHA!
>> WE WOULD HAVE, EXCEPT--
>> WE WERE HURT, TOO.
>> GRRR!
>> SEE?
I TOLD YOU WE SHOULD HAVE LEFT
THE FOOL WHERE HE WAS.
THEN AGAIN, I NEVER EXPECTED HIM
TO SHOW ME ANY GRATITUDE.
>> WHAT THE HECK HAPPENED TO
YOU?
YOU'RE TOTALLY SOAKED.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I HAD TO WASH OFF THAT WOLF
STENCH.
IT WAS RIGHT THROUGH MY CLOTHES.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> OH, DISGUSTING!
>> HEY, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
DISGUSTING!
>> SIMMER DOWN, KOGA.
>> OH.
>> LET'S GET OUT OF HERE,
KAGOME.
I CARRIED HIM TO A SAFE PLACE,
JUST LIKE YOU ASKED ME TO.
NOW IT'S THE IDIOT'S OWN PROBLEM
IF HE RECOVERS FROM HIS WOUNDS
OR DIES.
>> COME ON, INUYASHA.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TALK LIKE
THAT.
>> HANG ON A MINUTE!
YOU'RE ALWAYS CHEWING ME OUT
ABOUT SOMETHING!
SO HOW COME YOU NEVER SAY A WORD
TO THAT THANKLESS KOGA IDIOT?
>> HEY, QUIT YOUR WHINING ABOUT
THAT!
I'LL SAY THANKS ALL RIGHT!
THANK YOU, DEAR KAGOME.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE FROM PERIL.
>> I'M THE ONE YOU SHOULD BE
THANKING!
>> ALL YOU DID WAS CARRY ME.
>> GRRR!
>> HMM.
>> HAH!
HE LOOKS LIKE HE'S FEELING ALL
RIGHT TO ME.
>> WE CAN'T LEAVE HIM, THOUGH.
LOOK, HE CAN'T EVEN MOVE YET.
>> WHAT ABOUT MIROKU AND SANGO?
WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE THEM.
>> YEAH, GOOD POINT.
I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM
AFTER THEY WENT TO MT. HAKUREI.
>> THEY SHOULD BE BACK SOON,
DON'T YOU FIGURE?
>> I GUESS.
>> THEN COME ON, LET'S GO.
HUH?
A POISONOUS INSECT.
YOU GUYS STAY HERE.
I'LL CRUSH HIM BEFORE HE GIVES
THIS PLACE AWAY.
>> [BUZZING]
>> HEH.
>> HAKKAKU, GINTA, HOW ARE YOU
TWO FEELING NOW?
>> NOT QUITE BACK TO NORMAL YET.
>> WELL, WE GOT HIT PRETTY HARD,
ACTUALLY.
>> I'M SORRY.
I LOST MY FIRST-AID KIT, SO I
CAN'T TREAT YOUR WOUNDS.
>> OH, YOU DON'T NEED TO
APOLOGIZE!
>> WE WERE JUST GRATEFUL THAT
YOU EVEN THOUGHT TO ASK HOW WE
ARE.
>> [THINKING]
THEY'RE SURE HUMBLE, UNLIKE
KOGA.
HUH?
[SNIFFING]
>> [MEOWS]
>> HMM?
>> DO YOU SMELL IT, TOO, KAGOME?
>> NO, I SENSED A SACRED JEWEL
SHARD NEARBY.
YOU THOUGHT YOU SMELLED
SOMETHING, SHIPPO?
>> YEAH, I SMELLED SOMETHING
LIKE GUNPOWDER.
HUH?
AAAH!
>> THE RIVER!
>> HUH?
[WHIMPERS]
[SNIFFING]
SOMETHING'S COMING!
>> AAAH!
>> [BOTH SCREAMING]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> [BUZZING]
>> NO, YOU DON'T!
[GRUNTS]
[CHUCKLING]
HUH?
KAGOME!
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> IT'S THE BAND OF SEVEN!
>> I HAVE FILLED THE RIVER WITH
PLENTY OF OIL!
YOU'RE ALL TRAPPED!
>> IT'S RENKOTSU.
>> HIM AGAIN.
>> WE GOT TO MOVE HIM!
>> IT'S TOO DANGEROUS TO STAY.
>> [GROANING]
LOUSY SPECTER!
I'LL KILL HIM THIS TIME
FOR SURE!
>> KOGA!
>> NO, DON'T DO IT, KOGA!
>> HUH?
>> YOU'RE HURT TOO BADLY TO
FIGHT.
I'LL GET HIM.
THERE IT IS.
AAAH!
>> KAGOME!
>> INUYASHA!
>> [GRUNTS]
>> HUH?
>> DAMN THAT RENKOTSU!
HE MUST BE ANXIOUS FOR ME TO
KILL HIM, SINCE HE HASN'T WASTED
ANY TIME GETTING HERE!
>> HERE, INUYASHA, YOU SHOULD
WEAR THIS.
>> SHE'S RIGHT.
THE ROBE OF THE FIRE RAT WILL
PROTECT YOU FROM THE FIRE.
>> YOU TWO WEAR IT.
YOU CAN'T DEPEND ON THAT SKINNY
WOLF TO HELP YOU.
>> KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF RENKOTSU,
YOU MUTT!
IT'S MY JEWEL SHARDS THAT HE'LL
COME AFTER!
I'LL BE THE ONE TO KILL HIM!
>> KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT,
YOU IDIOT!
IF THE SHARDS FALL INTO HIS
HANDS, WE'LL ALL BE IN BIG
TROUBLE!
>> DAMN YOU!
>> PLEASE BE CAREFUL, INUYASHA.
RENKOTSU IS USING TWO JEWEL
SHARDS NOW.
>> NOT AS MANY AS BANKOTSU HAD.
>> [THINKING]
CURSE THAT INUYASHA!
WHAT'S HE DOING BACK ALREADY?
WHAT'S WRONG?!
TOO HOT FOR YOU IN THAT HOLE?!
>> AS IF!
JUST STAY WHERE YOU ARE, 'CAUSE
I'M COMIN' FOR YA!
>> UNREAL!
>> WHAT A JUMP!
>> WHAT MAKES YOU THINK I SHOULD
WAIT FOR YOU?
>> A CANNON?
>> YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO DODGE
THIS IN MID-AIR.
>> [GRUNTS]
AAAH!
>> INUYASHA!
SHE GOT HIM!
>> GREAT!
KILALA CAN'T BE HURT BY
THE FIRE!
>> WAY TO GO, KILALA!
NOW LET'S GO GET HIM!
>> I HAVE NO TIME FOR THE LIKES
OF YOU!
[GRUNTING]
>> KILALA, GET ABOVE HIM!
COMIN' FOR YOU, RENKOTSU!
>> BEAT YOU TO IT!
>> HUH?
[GROANING]
AAAH!
HUH?
>> HA HA HA HA!
>> INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
KAGOME, GET INSIDE THE CAVE!
>> HURRY!
>> DID I GET HIM?
HEH!
LOOKS LIKE MY FIRE CANNON
INCINERATED THE LOT OF THEM.
HMM.
AND NOW FOR THE SHARDS.
THEY'RE MINE AT LAST.
AAAH!
>> IMBECILE!
NOBODY'S DEAD IN HERE!
>> YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL, KOGA!
YOU MIGHT HAVE BEEN INCINERATED
IF KAGOME HADN'T COVERED YOU UP
WITH INUYASHA'S ROBE.
>> I'M NOT CRAZY ABOUT TOUCHING
ANYTHING BELONGING TO THAT
STINKY MUTT.
>> HA!
YOU THINK YOU'VE OUTWITTED ME?
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> THIS BATTLE IS FAR FROM OVER!
I'LL BLOW YOU TO HELL!
>> THOSE ARE FIRE BOMBS!
>> ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
IF YOU SET ONE OF THOSE OFF IN
HERE, IT'LL KILL YOU, TOO!
>> SILENCE!
THERE'S NO TURNING BACK FOR ME
NOW!
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> GRRR...
>> [THINKING]
IT'S TRUE.
I'VE BEEN USING THE SHARD THAT
GINKOTSU LEFT WITHOUT
PERMISSION.
BANKOTSU WILL KILL ME FOR IT.
>> I KNEW ALL ALONG THAT YOU
TOOK SHIKON JEWEL SHARDS FROM
THAT GIRL KAGOME AND HID THEM
FROM ME.
>> PLEASE DON'T BE ANGRY,
BIG BROTHER.
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO GIVE THEM
TO YOU ALL ALONG.
>> AH, THAT'S A WISE DECISION,
RENKOTSU.
YOU ARE SMART AFTER ALL,
IT SEEMS.
HOWEVER, DO NOT MAKE ANY MORE
MISTAKES.
>> KOGA, I'M GONNA HAVE THOSE
TWO SHARDS IN YOUR LEGS, NO
MATTER WHAT IT TAKES TO GET
THEM.
>> YOU CRETIN.
>> [THINKING]
ONCE I HAVE THOSE, I CAN BATTLE
BANKOTSU AND DEFEAT HIM.
THIS IS NO MEANINGLESS THREAT!
>> HE REALLY MEANS IT!
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> GRRR...
>> I WON'T FALL FOR THAT MOVE
TWICE.
>> LIGHT THAT, AND YOU'LL DIE
ALONG WITH US.
>> THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE WRONG!
[THINKING]
I'M SURE I WON'T DIE AS LONG
AS I HAVE THE JEWEL SHARDS.
THE ONLY ONES TO DIE WILL BE
YOU!
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> HA HA HA HA--
>> DON'T PUSH YOUR LUCK.
>> INUYASHA!
>> YOU AGAIN!
>> NOW'S YOUR ONLY CHANCE, WOLF!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> AAAH!
>> YEAH!
>> HE'S UP AGAIN, MUTT!
>> [GROANING]
>> [BOTH GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> NOT FOR LONG!
OH...
INUYASHA?
INUYASHA!
>> I'M SURE WE'LL FIND HIM SOON.
>> HE PROBABLY WASHED UP ON THE
RIVERBANK.
>> THAT'S IF THE MUTT WASN'T
BLOWN INTO A MILLION PIECES.
>> OH!
>> [MEOWS]
>> DON'T SAY THAT!
>> KOGA!
>> I'M JUST TELLING IT LIKE IT
IS.
BESIDES, IF THAT IDIOT HADN'T--
HMM?
>> OH...
>> [THINKING]
INUYASHA'S ROBE OF THE FIRE RAT
IS LIKE HIS ARMOR.
BUT HE WASN'T WEARING IT.
[CRYING]
>> KAGOME--
>> OH, NOW YOU MADE HER CRY.
>> NO, DON'T CRY, PLEASE?
>> IT'S ALL MY FAULT, 'CAUSE HE
LET ME WEAR THIS!
>> IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT, KAGOME.
I SAW WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO TOUCH THAT
STINKY ROBE, BUT HE FOR--
HMM?
>> YOU WERE SAYING WHO DIDN'T
WANT TO TOUCH IT?
>> [GASPS]
>> INUYASHA!
>> HEY, YOU MADE IT OUT ALIVE!
>> [CRYING]
>> HUH!
MY BODY'S BUILT DIFFERENTLY THAN
YOURS.
AND BESIDES, IN THE END,
IT TURNED OUT THAT THAT PUNK
RENKOTSU VALUED HIS LIFE MORE
THAN I WOULD HAVE GUESSED.
AT THE LAST MINUTE, HE THREW THE
FIRE BOMBS AWAY.
>> HMMPH!
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT HE'D DO
ALL ALONG.
YOU KNOW THE SAYING: "IDIOTS
NEVER DIE."
>> IDIOTS?
THINK YOU'LL GET AWAY WITH THAT?
>> WHAT, YOU WANT TO TAKE ME ON
NOW?
>> TODAY'S THE DAY.
I'M GONNA PUT YOUR LIGHTS OUT
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
>> WITH THAT BEAT-UP BODY OF
YOURS?
NOT LIKELY.
>> INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
HMM.
>> I WAS WORRIED.
ARE YOU REALLY OK?
YOU'RE NOT HURT?
>> HMM.
KAGOME.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO GET YOU ALL
UPSET.
>> YOU'RE NOT HURT OR ANYTHING?
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> [SOBBING]
>> HMM.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING, KOGA?
>> ARE YOU GONNA WALK AWAY?
>> JUST THIS ONCE, I'LL TURN
MY BACK.
KAGOME'S ALREADY UPSET ENOUGH
AS IT IS.
GET THIS STRAIGHT, THOUGH.
DON'T GO THINKING YOU'VE
DEFEATED ME, MUTT, 'CAUSE I'M
NEVER GONNA GIVE UP ON WINNING
KAGOME.
>> ONE GLANCE SHOULD BE ENOUGH
TO TELL YOU IT AIN'T GONNA
HAPPEN, YOU IDIOT.
>> GRRR!
HUH!
LOOK WHO'S TALKING!
YOU'RE ALL SMUG JUST 'CAUSE OF
ONE LITTLE HUG.
YOU'RE THE IDIOT!
>> HA!
YOU'RE SO JEALOUS.
SERVES YOU RIGHT, KOGA.
DOOFUS!
>> [THINKING]
IT'S KIND OF GETTING HARD
TO CRY.
>> ONE STUPID GUY CALLING THE
OTHER ONE STUPID.
>> YEAH, THEY'RE BOTH STUPID.
>> DUMB AS A SACK OF HAMMERS.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
>> [THINKING]
MY TEARS ARE DRYING UP FAST.
>> NOTHING IN THERE, EITHER.
>> NO SIGN OF DEMONS AT ALL.
>> THERE'S DEFINITELY A
CONNECTION BETWEEN NARAKU AND
THE BAND OF SEVEN, THOUGH.
AND IT'S A FACT THAT SAINT
HAKUSHIN WAS PROTECTING THE
RESURRECTED GROUP.
>> BUT WE STILL HAVEN'T FIGURED
OUT WHY.
>> RIGHT.
IF HE'S HELPING NARAKU BY
PUTTING THIS BARRIER AROUND MT.
HAKUREI, THEN THAT LEADS US TO
ONE CONCLUSION.
>> YES, THAT NARAKU IS HIDING
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
>> LET'S GO ON TO THE TOP OF THE
MOUNTAIN FOR STARTERS.
IF WE GO BACK EMPTY-HANDED,
WE'LL HEAR ABOUT IT FROM
INUYASHA.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> ONE MORE THING.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT
THIS BARRIER.
HERE WE ARE, FINALLY ALONE
TOGETHER, AND I CAN'T EVEN MAKE
A MOVE TOWARD HER.
I CAN'T TAKE IT MUCH LONGER.
UH...
HUH?
OK.
HMM.
>> [THINKING]
DAMN IT!
I'VE FAILED AGAIN!
I DIDN'T MANAGE TO STEAL KOGA'S
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
IF WORD GETS OUT THAT I'M USING
GINKOTSU'S JEWEL SHARD, THEN
BANKOTSU WILL KILL ME FOR
CERTAIN.
NOW WHAT DO I DO?
>> [BUZZING]
>> A SAIMYOUSHOU!
HUH?
[GASPS]
>> BANKOTSU, THIS IS A SURPRISE.
>> HEY, RENKOTSU.
I HEARD THE NEWS FROM THE
INSECTS.
OUR POOR FRIEND GINKOTSU BIT
THE DUST, DID HE?
>> UH, YEAH.
>> THAT'S A TERRIBLE SHAME,
ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING ALL THE
TIME YOU SPENT RECONSTRUCTING
HIM SO ADEPTLY.
>> UH...
>> I'M GLAD ABOUT ONE THING.
AT LEAST YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
>> UH...
>> SUIKOTSU WENT AFTER
SESSHOMARU, BUT NOW HE'S DEAD,
AS WELL.
>> SUIKOTSU?
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
THERE'S ONLY YOU, ME, AND
JAKOTSU.
JUST THE THREE OF US ARE LEFT.
AND THAT'S WHERE WE STAND.
I'M GOING TO BE DEPENDING ON YOU
NOW MORE THAN EVER.
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S BE ON OUR WAY.
>> [THINKING]
THAT CREEP BANKOTSU.
DIDN'T HE EVEN NOTICE GINKOTSU'S
JEWEL SHARD?
HMMPH!
IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S GOT SOME USE
FOR ME YET.
I GUESS I GOT A REPRIEVE THIS
TIME.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, MIROKU?
>> LOOK AT THIS.
THE PATH ENDS.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF SOMEONE HACKED
OFF PART OF THE MOUNTAIN.
>> OVER THERE, MIROKU.
>> HMM?
A CAVE.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE PATH USED TO
LEAD UP TO THAT CAVE.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GO IN?
>> CAN YOU GET US UP THERE?
>> I CAN TRY.
[GRUNTS]
EXCELLENT.
ALL RIGHT.
>> WOW.
>> HERE!
CATCH ON TO THIS, MIROKU!
>> VERY IMPRESSIVE, SANGO.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> IT LEADS FAR INTO THE
MOUNTAIN.
>> I SENSE A DEMONIC AURA HERE.
LET'S GO, SANGO.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
NARAKU IS DEEP INSIDE THIS CAVE.
>> HMM.
>> [THINKING]
DAMN THAT NARAKU.
HOW LONG IS HE GOING TO KEEP ME
SHUT UP IN THIS PLACE?
>> KAGURA.
>> OH, KANNA, IT'S YOU.
BOY, YOU HAVE SURE GOT IT GOOD.
YOU DON'T EMANATE ANY DEMONIC
AURA, SO YOU CAN COME AND GO ON
SACRED GROUND.
I CAN'T EVEN TAKE ONE STEP
OUTSIDE THAT ANNOYING BARRIER
BECAUSE IF I DO, I'LL END UP
BEING PURIFIED.
DAMN IT ALL.
>> THEY'RE COMING.
>> THOSE TWO--THE MONK AND THE
DEMON SLAYER.
HMM, ISN'T THIS INTERESTING?
WE'RE LONG OVERDUE FOR A LITTLE
TROUBLEMAKING.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> A DEMONIC AURA IS DEEP INSIDE
MT. HAKUREI.
>> NARAKU IS IN HERE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE TWO HUMANS
ACTUALLY CAME IN HERE ALONE.
>> KAGURA!
>> YOU'RE BRAVE, BUT YOU'RE NOT
GETTING OUT OF HERE ALIVE.
>> NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS!
MIROKU, DON'T SUCK THEM UP OR
THE POISON WILL--
>> IF IT'LL EXTEND YOUR LIFE,
MY DEAR, I'LL DO IT.
WIND TUNNEL!
>> NEXT TIME, "INTO THE DEPTHS
OF MT. HAKUREI."
>> FORGIVE ME, SANGO, BUT YOU,
AT LEAST, MUST LIVE ON!