- DAMN IT ALL!
ISN'T THERE SOME WAY
I CAN DESTROY HIM?
IMPOSSIBLE!
- IT APPEARS THAT I'M GETTING
ACCUSTOMED TO THIS BODY OF MINE.
- UNH!
- INUYASHA, LOOK OUT!
AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- AAH!
AAH!
UNH!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
CAN'T MOVE?
- OH, SAVE IT.
AAH!
UNH!
UNH.
[ALL GASPING]
- DAMN YOU!
- INUYASHA, THIS TIME I'M GOING
TO SLICE YOU TO PIECES.
- AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- COME TO ME.
- I'LL DESTROY YOU!
GOD, YOU BASTARD!
WIND SCAR!
UNH!
HUH!
HANDS OFF.
DAMN IT!
HE'S NOT DEAD YET.
- THIS WILL NEVER
COME TO AN END.
- HUH! LOOK AT THAT!
A SPIDER!
- HE'S TRANSFORMING AGAIN.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
HIS BODY IS MADE OF?
- NARAKU IS BASICALLY
AN AMALGAMATION OF DEMONS
BONDED INTO ONE BY
THE BANDIT ONIGUMO.
IF MUSO WAS CREATED FROM
NARAKU'S FLESH, THEN PERHAPS...
- PERHAPS SEVERAL OTHER DEMONS
WERE RELEASED FROM NARAKU
WHEN MUSO WAS EXPELLED.
- IS HE DIFFERENT FROM US?
IS HE SPECIAL SOMEHOW...
EVEN TO NARAKU?
- WHY IS MUSO ABLE
TO REGENERATE?
WHAT'S HIS SECRET?
- WHY, YOU...
- I TOLD YOU
YOU WOULD NEVER DESTROY ME.
- CURSE YOU!
YAAH!
UNH!
AAH!
[GASP]
- I CAN'T WATCH!
ISN'T THERE SOMETHING WE CAN DO?
- INUYASHA IS
STARTING TO FATIGUE.
THAT'S TO BE EXPECTED
AFTER USING THE WIND SCAR
SO MANY TIMES.
- YEAH. HE'S ALSO WITHSTOOD
MUSO'S RELENTLESS ATTACKS.
HE CAN'T TAKE MUCH MORE OF THIS.
- TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR
PATHETIC SELF, INUYASHA.
HAD ENOUGH ALREADY?
- INUYASHA, USE
THE BACKLASH WAVE!
USE IT ON MUSO TO
BLOW HIM TO BITS!
[GRUNT]
- DON'T YOU THINK I WOULD
HAVE DONE THAT ALREADY
IF I COULD, SHIPPO?
- IT WON'T WORK ON HIM?
- THE MOVE UTILIZES
THE OPPONENT'S DEMONIC AURA,
BUT MUSO'S ONLY BEEN
USING BRUTE STRENGTH.
- THE WIND SCAR'S
THE ANSWER, INUYASHA.
- BUT, MIROKU...
- TRY STRIKING HIM ONE MORE TIME
WITH YOUR WIND SCAR!
- NO NEED TO TELL ME THAT!
- MMM!
- WIND SCAR!
AAH!
- AARGH!
[PANTING]
- HOW'S THAT?
HE'S COMING BACK!
THIS IS GOING TO GO ON FOREVER,
AS LONG AS HE CAN REGENERATE.
- INUYASHA...
THE PIECES OF MUSO'S
FLESH ALWAYS ACCUMULATE
AT THE SPIDER MARKS.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT--
SPIDER MARKS?
- LOOK. THE SPIDER-SHAPED
SCAR ON HIS BACK--
MUSO REGENERATES BY DRAWING
HIS PARTS TOWARD THAT SCAR.
THE MARK WAS PULSATING.
THAT'S PROBABLY
WHERE HIS HEART IS.
- I GET IT.
THEN IT'S WORTH A TRY
TO AIM RIGHT THERE.
- YOU'RE WASTING
YOUR TIME, INUYASHA.
YOU'RE ALREADY OUT OF BREATH,
AND WE'VE ONLY JUST STARTED.
- THE TRACK OF THE WIND SCAR
GOES STRAIGHT TO MUSO.
I'LL USE IT TO STRIKE
INTO HIS HEART.
- DIE, INUYASHA!
- THIS IS IT.
- DANCE OF BLADES!
- KAGURA!
- AAAAH!
[ALL SHOUTING]
- HUH?
- IS IT OVER?
- HARDLY.
KAGURA USED HER DANCE OF BLADES
TO DIVERT MY WIND SCAR
SO IT WOULDN'T STRIKE
MUSO'S HEART.
- AT LEAST WE'VE
DISCOVERED ONE THING:
MUSO'S VULNERABILITY
IS HIS HEART.
- HMPH!
AND HE'S NOT HIDING
THAT FACT, EITHER.
[BUZZING]
COME ON! LET'S FOLLOW THEM.
- RIGHT.
SANGO, STAY HERE AND LOOK AFTER
KAGOME AND THE OTHERS.
- WILL DO.
- DON'T WORRY, MIROKU.
WE'LL LOOK AFTER THEM.
[PANTING]
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THE BANDIT
ONIGUMO HAS COME BACK AGAIN
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
- I DON'T THINK MUSO
IS JUST ANOTHER ONE
OF NARAKU'S CREATIONS.
- I AGREE. MUSO HAS
ONIGUMO'S HEART.
- BUT STILL, DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S KIND OF STRANGE?
- HOW?
- WHY WOULD NARAKU LET MUSO GO?
- NARAKU TRIED TO GET
RID OF ONIGUMO'S HEART
BECAUSE IT STILL LOVED KIKYO.
THEN NARAKU COULD
TRY TO DESTROY HER.
FOR HIM, ONIGUMO
WAS A LIABILITY.
THAT MUST BE WHY HE CAST
ONIGUMO FROM HIS BODY.
- YET NARAKU IS USING KAGURA
AND THE POISON INSECTS TO
PROTECT MUSO.
WHY WOULD HE DO SUCH A THING?
- YEAH, RIGHT, ESPECIALLY SEEING
AS HIS OTHER INCARNATIONS
WERE SO DISPOSABLE.
- COULD IT POSSIBLY MEAN THAT
NARAKU STILL NEEDS ONIGUMO?
[THUNDER]
- AHH.
DAMN THAT INUYASHA.
I WAS SO CLOSE TO KILLING HIM.
WHERE AM I?
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- ONIGUMO,
OR SHALL I SAY MUSO...
IMAGINE MEETING EACH OTHER
LIKE THIS, FACE TO FACE.
- YOU--I KNOW YOU.
- HMM!
- ARE YOU NARAKU?
- DID YOU ENJOY THE OUTSIDE
WORLD AFTER 50 YEARS' ABSENCE?
- 50 YEARS?
IS THAT WHAT YOU SAID?
- MUSO, I DEMAND
THAT YOU RETURN TO ME.
- YOU MUST BE JOKING!
- THE THOUGHT
REPULSES ME, AS WELL,
BUT YOU WERE RELEASED
TOO EARLY, I'M AFRAID...
AND THAT IS WHY YOU MUST
COME BACK TO ME NOW.
- TOO EARLY?
HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT
AFTER KEEPING ME
LOCKED UP FOR 50 YEARS!
- IT COULDN'T HAVE SEEMED
BUT A SECOND TO YOU.
- I REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED NOW.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO KILLED
KIKYO 50 YEARS AGO!
- AND IN YOUR TWISTED GREED,
YOU SUMMONED THE DEMONS
RIGHT TO YOUR SIDE.
THOSE SAME DEMONS WHICH DEVOURED
YOUR FLESH WISHED TO KILL KIKYO.
- IT WAS YOUR DESIRE,
NOT THEIRS!
- I WAS NOT THE ONE TO BLAME.
I AM NARAKU, AND YOU
SHOULD KNOW THAT BY NOW.
- I'VE HEARD ENOUGH!
THE ONLY THING I DESIRED
WAS TO MAKE KIKYO MY WOMAN.
DAMN IT!
- KIKYO HAS BEEN RESURRECTED.
SHE LOOKS EXACTLY
AS SHE DID BEFORE.
- SHE'S...BACK?
- YES, ALTHOUGH SHE'S NOT
EXACTLY THE SAME AS BEFORE.
- KIKYO IS ALIVE?
[NARAKU CHUCKLES]
- WANT HER?
- WHERE IS SHE? WHERE IS KIKYO?
- I'M AFRAID I CANNOT
GRANT YOUR WISH.
RETURN TO ME.
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
- I'LL NEVER GO BACK TO YOU!
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
THIS TIME, I WILL
MAKE KIKYO MY WOMAN!
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- AAH!
PERSISTENT BASTARD!
GO AWAY AND LEAVE ME ALONE NOW!
- NOT THIS TIME.
[GRUNTING]
- MUSO IS TRYING TO
ESCAPE FROM NARAKU?
IS HE PLANNING TO DEFY HIM?
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
- I SEE.
NARAKU DOESN'T CONTROL
MUSO'S LIFE.
SO THAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN HIM AND ME.
- AAH!
UNH!
- YOU WILL RETURN TO MY BODY.
- WHAT'S GOING ON, NARAKU?
- HMM.
INUYASHA.
- WHAT'S THE DEAL?
YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY HAVE ANY
USE FOR ONIGUMO'S HUMAN HEART.
YOU DON'T NEED HIM.
THAT'S WHY YOU DUG HIM
OUT OF YOUR FLESH
AND CAST HIM OUT.
SO TELL ME, HOW COME
YOU'RE TRYING TO
TAKE HIM BACK NOW?
- I THOUGHT MUSO WOULD
BE ABLE TO KILL YOU,
BUT IT SEEMS THAT
I WAS MISTAKEN,
SO HE'S COMING BACK.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
- NOTHING'S THAT
SIMPLE WITH YOU.
SOMETHING VERY PRECIOUS
GOT MIXED IN
AND ACCIDENTALLY
RELEASED WITH MUSO.
OTHERWISE, THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'D TAKE BACK HIS HEART
AFTER YOU WENT TO ALL THAT
TROUBLE TO GET RID OF IT.
- OH, MY. HOW CLEVER.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
ACTUALLY USING THAT HEAD
OF YOURS TO THINK.
WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
- I CAN DESTROY MUSO ANYTIME,
WHICH MEANS YOU'RE ON THE TOP
OF MY TO-DO LIST.
AAH!
AAAH!
UNH!
AAH!
[SWORDS CLASHING]
UNH!
- IS HE SERIOUS?
- YAAH!
- DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
KAGURA, GO AFTER MUSO.
DON'T LET HIM ESCAPE.
[PANTING]
- MUSO AND I WERE BOTH CREATED
FROM NARAKU'S FLESH.
I ACT ACCORDING TO
NARAKU'S WISHES,
BUT MUSO IS ESCAPING.
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
- AAH!
UNH! YAH!
AAH...YAAH!
[PANTING]
- INUYASHA!
- WHAT TOOK YOU?
- WHAT'S NARAKU DOING HERE?
- HE'S TRYING TO TAKE MUSO BACK.
- HUH?
- I'LL BET RELEASING MUSO
MADE YOU A LOT WEAKER
THAN YOU USED TO BE, NARAKU.
AM I RIGHT?
[WIND BLOWS]
UNH!
AAH!
DIE!
UHH!
- DON'T PRESUME TO
UNDERSTAND ME, INUYASHA.
YOU ARE NOTHING.
- AH!
- OH!
[LAUGHING]
- MUSO!
- IT CAN'T BE!
HE KILLED NARAKU!
- HE DID IT!
- HA HA HA HA HA!
YOU FOOL.
YOU DIDN'T THINK I'D LET
YOU GET AWAY, DID YOU?
- HMM.
- HUH?
MY ARM'S BEING ABSORBED!
- YOU SAVED ME
THE TROUBLE, MUSO.
I NEED YOU TO COME
BACK TO ME NOW.
- DAMN YOU!
UNH!
[GRUNTING]
NO! I'VE LOST CONTROL
OF MY BODY!
ARRGH!
LET ME GO!
RELEASE ME AT ONCE!
- WILL THAT BE THE FATE I SUFFER
IF I SHOULD CHOOSE TO
DEFY HIM, AS WELL?
- STOP!
LET ME SEE KIKYO!
I MUST SEE KIKYO!
- OH!
- KIKYO!
KIKYO!
[SCREAMING]
- SUCH BITTERNESS,
SUCH FESTERING GREED.
GIVE IT UP, MUSO.
KIKYO IS EXACTLY
THE SAME AS YOU--
MADE OF NOTHING
BUT CLAY AND DIRT.
HER SOUL IS A MERE
PHANTOM OF THE PAST.
- AAAH!
- HE ABSORBED MUSO!
[LAUGHS]
YOU SEE, I REQUIRE ONIGUMO
AS A LINK FOR MY OWN BODY.
YOUR CONJECTURE WAS INDEED
ACCURATE, INUYASHA.
- A LINK?
- ANSWER ME THIS, NARAKU:
YOU'VE SWALLOWED
ONIGUMO'S HEART AGAIN,
SO DOES THAT MAKE
YOU A HALF-DEMON?
- WHY WOULD YOU ASK THAT?
- A WHILE BACK,
THE IMPENETRABLE BARRIER
AROUND YOUR CASTLE WEAKENED.
INUYASHA AND KOGA--IN FACT,
ANYONE WITH A KEEN NOSE--
COULD FIND IT.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE WANTED THAT.
- WHAT'S MIROKU
TRYING TO FIND OUT?
- I SEE, MONK.
SO YOU WISH TO KNOW
IF EVEN I HAVE
A PERIOD OF WEAKNESS,
DON'T YOU--
IF I AM INDEED LIKE
ALL HALF-DEMONS?
- I KNOW THAT YOUR
POWERS HAD WEAKENED
THAT TIME, NARAKU.
- HUH?
[CHUCKLES]
BUT EXACTLY WHEN THAT OCCURS IS
A HALF-DEMON'S DEEPEST SECRET.
LET'S HEAR ABOUT YOU, INUYASHA.
- WHAT?!
- DO YOU, LIKE SO MANY
OTHER HALF-DEMONS,
LOSE YOUR POWERS AND HIDE
IN FEAR OF YOUR ENEMIES
DURING SUCH TIMES?
- UH...WHY, YOU!
- INTERESTING.
JUDGING FROM WHAT NARAKU JUST
SAID, KAGURA HASN'T TOLD HIM
THAT INUYASHA'S NIGHT OF
WEAKNESS IS DURING THE NEW MOON.
- MONK.
- HUH?
- AS YOU SURMISED, I HAVE
PERIODS WHEN I CANNOT MOVE.
HOWEVER, I CHOOSE
THAT TIME MYSELF...
OF MY OWN WILL.
- WHAT?
- THERE IS NO WAY
YOU CAN DO THAT!
- YOU ARE VASTLY
DIFFERENT FROM ME
BECAUSE YOU WERE BORN OF A HUMAN
AND A DEMON, INUYASHA.
DON'T YOU AGREE, KAGURA?
[GASP]
- WHEN I FOUND HIM IN A CELLAR,
IT LOOKED LIKE HE WAS
RECONSTRUCTING HIS BODY.
- DURING MY TIMES OF WEAKNESS,
I EXPERIMENT.
WHAT IS STRONG, I TAKE
AND MAKE STRONGER.
I CAST OUT THE WEAK AND BECOME
EVEN MORE POWERFUL.
- HE CAN RECONSTRUCT
HIS OWN BODY?
- DAMN!
[CHUCKLING]
- I'M A HALF-DEMON RIGHT NOW--
THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
BUT UNLIKE SOME OTHER
HALF-DEMONS,
I DON'T LOSE MY POWERS
AND COWER IN FEAR.
- HUH! I'M SURE YOU COULD TALK
ABOUT YOURSELF FOR DAYS,
BUT I'VE GOT BETTER
THINGS ON MY MIND!
UNH! DIE!
UNH!
WHAT'S THAT?
- A BARRIER.
- HUH! IT WON'T STOP ME.
WIND SCAR!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- THE WIND SCAR DIDN'T WORK.
I'M PRETTY CERTAIN THAT
NARAKU'S BARRIERS WEREN'T
THAT POWERFUL BEFORE.
- I'LL SAY IT AGAIN: I ONLY
CONTINUE TO GROW IN POWER.
[RUMBLING]
- GET BACK NOW! IT'S MIASMA!
[BUZZING]
- AAH!
- HE'S GONE.
- IT SEEMS AS THOUGH NARAKU
WAS SPEAKING THE TRUTH ABOUT
HIS POWERS.
- YEAH. I TURN INTO NOTHING
BUT A WEAK MORTAL
ON THE NIGHT OF THE NEW MOON,
BUT NARAKU'S DIFFERENT FROM ME?
- YES.
IF NARAKU IS ABLE TO RECONSTRUCT
HIMSELF AND GET STRONGER,
THEN I'M AFRAID WE MIGHT
BE IN REAL TROUBLE.
[WIND BLOWS]
- I FEEL AN OMINOUS WIND.
- HMM?
IT'S NARAKU.
I KNOW IT IS HIM.
- WHAT IS IT, LADY KIKYO?
- HUH?
IT'S NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT,
SO I THINK IT'S BEST IF
YOU REST AT EASE, OLD MAN.
- OF COURSE.
- WHAT?
YOU MEAN, NARAKU'S BARRIER
HELD OFF THE WIND SCAR?
- HUMPH!
- YES. NARAKU IS DEFINITELY
BECOMING STRONGER.
ON TOP OF THAT,
HE'S A HALF-DEMON,
BUT UNLIKE INUYASHA, HE
DOESN'T LOSE HIS POWERS
DURING THE NEW MOON.
INSTEAD, NARAKU SAYS
HE CAN CHOOSE HIS DAY.
- ARE YOU SAYING WE CAN'T
KNOW EXACTLY WHEN HIS POWERS
WILL BE WEAKENED?
- CORRECT.
I THOUGHT WE'D BE
ABLE TO DEFEAT HIM
IF WE ONLY KNEW WHEN HE
WAS RENDERED POWERLESS.
- HUH. WHAT'S EVERYBODY
GETTING ALL SERIOUS ABOUT?
AT LEAST WE KNOW NOW THAT HE
DOES HAVE A PERIOD OF WEAKNESS.
I HAVE TO GET STRONGER
THAN HIM, THAT'S ALL.
JUST LET ME HANDLE THINGS.
- INUYASHA, I'VE NEVER
HEARD YOU SOUND SO POSITIVE.
- I'M ALWAYS POSITIVE,
YOU CREEP!
- IF THIS IS HIS GOOD SIDE,
I'D HATE TO SEE HIM GLOOMY.
- TRUE.
UH-OH. I FORGOT MY STUFF!
- WHAT STUFF?
- BY THE WELL.
I HAVE TO GO GET IT.
[GASP]
- WHAT IS IT?
HUH?
- IT'S GORGEOUS!
- HUH! WHAT'S SO SPECIAL
ABOUT THE STARS?
- IN MY TIME, YOU NEVER
SEE THEM THIS CLEARLY.
- OH, YEAH?
- I UNDERSTAND NOW.
I AM KIKYO, AND YET NOT KIKYO.
THAT'S WHY I RESISTED.
YET, WHY...WHY DOES
MY HEART YEARN SO?
INUYASHA.
[NO AUDIO]
WHICH DOES MY HEART WISH FOR?
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- LISTEN, SHIPPO.
INUYASHA HEADED OUT
ALONE TO SEE TOTOSAI.
- YOU MEAN, THE OLD MAN
WHO FORGED THE TETSUSAIGA?
- INUYASHA WANTS TO LEARN
A TECHNIQUE TO BREAK THROUGH
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
- THAT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
WHAT A FOOL.
- I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- KNOWING TOTOSAI,
HE'S NOT GOING TO MAKE
IT EASY FOR INUYASHA.
- NEXT TIME,
"TOTOSAI'S RIGID TRAINING."
- WHAT? INUYASHA HAS
A FELLOW DISCIPLE?