>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL
THE SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> KOGA IS SERIOUSLY HURT
DURING HIS DESPERATE BATTLE WITH
THE BAND OF 7, AND WE DISCOVER
THAT THE SACRED BARRIER
AROUND MOUNT HAKUREI HAS THE
POWER TO SLOW DOWN EVEN
SESSHOMARU.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRYTALE.
>> "INUYASHA!"
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> HERE.
>> HEY, DON'T BE SO ROUGH.
>> HUMPH.
>> HE'S RIGHT.
KOGA'S HURT, REMEMBER?
YOU COULD TREAT HIM A LITTLE
MORE GENTLY, YOU KNOW.
>> GO EASY ON HIM?
I SHOULD BE TAKING THE SHARDS
FROM HIS SCRAWNY LEGS INSTEAD OF
SAVING HIM.
I SHOULD'VE JUST ABANDONED HIM.
>> YEAH.
SO HOW COME YOU DIDN'T DO IT?
>> LIKE I'D TAKE ADVANTAGE OF A
GUY WHO CAN'T EVEN DEFEND
HIMSELF.
>> INUYASHA...
>> "THE EXPOSED FACE OF TRUTH."
>> [GRUNTS]
>> [SCREAMS]
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> DAMN IT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY HAVE I LOST CONTROL OF MY
BODY?
IT'S THOSE KIDS!
>> SUIKOTSU, SESSHOMARU IS
COMING.
>> REALLY?
>> KILL THE KIDS LATER.
RIGHT NOW, WE NEED TO LURE
SESSHOMARU INTO THE BARRIER.
>> YES, I KNOW.
>> I FOUND THEM.
THEY'RE JUST UP AHEAD.
>> WAIT FOR ME, MY LORD.
AH!
AAGH!
[GASPING]
LORD SESSHOMARU, IT'S A TRAP!
THAT'S WHY THEY'VE ABDUCTED
RIN, SO THEY CAN LURE YOU INTO
THE BARRIER!
DON'T GO ANY FURTHER!
AH!
HUH?
LORD SESSHOMARU!
DOESN'T HE FEEL ANYTHING?
AM I THE ONLY ONE FEELING SICK?
IF HE CAN HANDLE IT, I CAN.
I CAN DO ANYTHING ONCE I PUT MY
MIND TO IT.
AH!
THEN AGAIN, MAYBE NOT.
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> IT'S LADY KIKYO.
>> CHILDREN, I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU
SAFE.
I'M TOO LATE.
SUIKOTSU DID THIS, DIDN'T HE?
>> YES.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE DOCTOR CAME BACK LOOKING SO
KIND.
>> HE'S CHANGED THOUGH, INSIDE.
>> HMM.
MOUNT HAKUREI NO LONGER HAS ANY
EFFECT ON SUIKOTSU, WHICH MEANS
SACRED JEWEL SHARD HAS BECOME
MORE TAINTED.
>> HE'S NOT FOLLOWING.
>> I GUESS THE BARRIER IS TOO
STRONG FOR EVEN SESSHOMARU TO
MAKE IT THIS FAR.
>> HEH, I WOULDN'T SAY SO.
>> HUH?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, YOU'VE COME!
>> HE CUT US OFF.
>> DAMN IT, REG.
YOU'RE A DEMON, YET THE BARRIER
ISN'T EFFECTING YOU.
[SIGHS]
THEN MAYBE THIS WILL!
AH!
>> MY LORD, YOU'RE WOUNDED.
>> HA HA HA.
I THOUGHT SO.
YOUR SKILLS HAVE BEEN DULLED BY
THE BARRIER.
>> YOU MUST LEAVE THE VILLAGE AT
ONCE, CHILDREN, AT LEAST FOR
NOW.
>> LADY KIKYO, WE HAVE NOWHERE
TO GO.
>> LISTEN WELL:
IF YOU STAY HERE ANY LONGER,
MISFORTUNES ARE SURE TO BEFALL
YOU.
[WHINNIES]
>> I KNOW ONE THING, KIKYO;
DEAD PEOPLE LIKE YOU AND I WILL
PROBABLY SHARE THE SAME FATE.
LET'S BOTH JUST ENJOY THE TIME
WE HAVE HERE ON EARTH.
I HAVE NO INTERESTS IN THE
SO-CALLED OTHER WORLDS.
I DO AS I PLEASE WITH NO FEAR OF
THE AFTERLIFE.
>> LOOK, MIROKU.
>> WHAT IS IT?
YOU SEE SOMETHING OVER THERE?
>> IS IT POSSIBLE WE'VE GOTTEN
LOST?
THIS IS THE SAME PATH WE JUST
TOOK.
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> THE FASTER WE TURN AROUND,
THE EASIER IT'LL BE TO
BACKTRACK.
>> PERHAPS.
THIS CAVE IS INCREDIBLE.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE A MAZE IN HERE.
>> HMM.
NOW I GET IT.
YOU DON'T KNOW THE WAY OUT OF
HERE, DO YOU?
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU?
CAN YOU LEAD US TO THE OUTSIDE?
>> I WAS JUST FOLLOWING YOU.
I DIDN'T THINK I HAD TO REMEMBER
THE WAY.
>> THERE YOU GO AGAIN, ALWAYS
BLAMING OTHERS.
HUMPH.
>> [SIGHING]
>> NOTHING HERE.
>> HUH?
>> YOU SAW THAT TOO, JUST NOW?
>> I DID.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF IT WANTS US TO
FOLLOW IT.
>> IT MAY BE SOME KIND OF TRAP.
>> I DON'T SENSE ANY DEMONIC
AURA.
BESIDES, SANGO, YOU REMEMBER HOW
THE OLD SAYING GOES, "NOTHING
VENTURED, NOTHING GAINED."
>> I CAN'T LET THOSE TWO GO ANY
FURTHER.
PLEASE, JUST FOLLOW ME.
>> AAGH!
LOOK, SESSHOMARU!
>> BE QUIET.
>> YOUR PRIDE IS TRULY
ASTOUNDING, ESPECIALLY SINCE YOU
CAN BARELY EVEN STAND...
ALL THANKS TO THE BARRIER!
[GRUNTING]
THAT WRETCH.
ACTING LIKE HE'S PERFECTLY FINE
WHEN HE'S NOT.
HE'S GRADUALLY TRYING TO MOVE
AWAY FROM THE BARRIER THOUGH...
WHICH MEANS IT IS HARD ON HIM.
HEY, SUIKOTSU,
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T MOVE AWAY
FROM THE MOUNTAIN.
>> I DON'T NEED TO BE REMINDED,
JAKOTSU.
YOU JUST CONCENTRATE ON YOUR END
AND GET RID OF THE MENACE.
MAKE IT FAST, BECAUSE I'M JUST
ITCHING TO SLAUGHTER THIS LITTLE
BRAT.
[SIGHS]
I COULDN'T KILL THOSE VILLAGE
KIDS BECAUSE THE DOCTOR
INTERFERED.
THIS TIME, I'LL DO IT FOR
CERTAIN.
>> HELP, LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> DON'T DO ANYTHING FUNNY.
ONE WRONG MOVE FROM YOU, AND THE
KID IS DEAD.
YOU GOT THAT?
>> IT'S FUNNY.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME, IF
YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
>> IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK?
HUH?
HMM.
>> WHY YOU ARROGANT WRETCH,
WHAT'S SO DAMN FUNNY?
YOU'RE HARDLY IN ANY POSITION TO
BE LAUGHING!
OH?!
HE THREW HIS SWORD AWAY.
OH!
[GROANING]
>> [STRAINING]
LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
>> [GROANING]
UP CLOSE LIKE THIS,
YOU REALLY ARE ATTRACTIVE.
[CHUCKLES]
NICE TRY, BUT NO LUCK.
WE CANNOT BE SLAIN LIKE NORMAL
MORTALS.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I'VE WAITED LONG ENOUGH.
I'M GOING TO KILL HER NOW.
THAT IDIOT DOCTOR.
HE'S TOO SCARED TO COME OUT
BECAUSE OF MY INJURY.
>> [GASPS]
>> IT'S INCREDIBLE.
THIS URGE I FEEL TO KILL IS
OVERWHELMING.
>> YOU FOOL!
IT'S TOO LATE TO SAVE HER.
>> NOW DIE!
HUH?
[GRUNTS]
>> SUIKOTSU, THE LIGHT FROM YOUR
SACRED JEWEL SHARD IS TAINTED
BLACK.
YOU ARE NO LONGER.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> OH, THAT DEAD PRIESTESS
AGAIN.
SHE SCARES ME MORE THAN ANYONE.
>> LADY KIKYO, IT'S YOU.
>> HUH?
DOCTOR SUIKOTSU.
>> AT LAST...
I HAVE RETURNED.
THE TAINTED DARK LIGHT
BLOCKED MY WAY.
I COULDN'T RECOVER MYSELF.
>> DID MY SACRED ARROW PURIFY
THE SHARD?
WHAT DO I DO WITH HIM NOW?
MUST I KILL HIM?
>> LADY KIKYO.
>> HMM?
>> PLEASE REMOVE THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD FROM MY NECK.
DO THAT FOR ME...
THEN ALL WILL BE OVER.
I CAN REST IN PEACE.
MY LAST WISH IS TO BE RELEASED.
>> YOU ARE CERTAIN?
DO YOU CHOOSE DEATH?
>> I'M CERTAIN.
I FINALLY REMEMBER WHAT
HAPPENED.
I DIED BEFORE, LONG AGO IN THE
PAST.
>> [CHILDREN SINGING]
>> WHEN I WAS ALIVE BEFORE,
I WAS TORMENTED BY UNCERTAINTY.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS RIGHT AND
WHAT WAS WRONG.
I CAN SAVE HER.
I KNOW I CAN SAVE HER.
>> DOCTOR, IT'S TOO LATE
FOR THAT CHILD.
JUST LET HER DIE, AND LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE.
>> DON'T BE RIDICULOUS, THERE'S
STILL HOPE.
>> BUT THE SAMURAI ARE HEADING
THIS WAY.
THEY'LL KILL US!
>> FLEE IF YOU WANT, BUT I'M
GOING TO SAVE THIS CHILD.
>> AH!
YOU KILLED HER.
WHY?
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?
>> I PUT HER OUT OF HER MISERY.
YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL.
>> HUH?!
>> JUST FOLLOWING OUR LORD'S
INSTRUCTIONS.
HE INSTRUCTED US TO KILL EVERY
LAST PERSON IN THE VILLAGE.
>> [GASPING]
>> HA HA HA.
>> NO, NO!
STAY AWAY!
>> HA HA HA.
[GRUNTS]
>> I WAS A PHYSICIAN WHO HAD
SWORN TO SAVE PEOPLE'S LIVES,
AND YET, I HAD KILLED SOMEONE
WITH MY OWN HANDS.
LOOKING BACK, I WAS PROBABLY
HARDER ON MYSELF THAN ANYONE
ELSE WOULD'VE BEEN.
I COULDN'T FORGIVE MYSELF.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
[SCREAMING]
THAT'S WHEN IT HAPPENED...
WHEN I HEARD THE VOICE.
>> WHY DON'T YOU STOP ACTING THE
PART OF A SAINT?
YOU REALLY AREN'T INTERESTED IN
HELPING PEOPLE!
>> HUH?
>> DEEP INSIDE, YOU WANT
TO KILL.
YOU'RE JUST ITCHING TO KILL AND
KILL!
>> SUDDENLY, IT BECAME CLEAR TO
ME.
THE PERSON WHO WAS SPEAKING WAS
ME, MYSELF.
>> [MAN SCREAMING]
>> [WOMAN SCREAMING]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> AN INCREDIBLE EVIL LURKED IN
MY HEART...
>> [SCREAMS CONTINUE]
>> ...AND THAT EVIL MADE ME
KILL OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
NOT LONG AFTERWARD, I MET
BANKOTSU AND JOINED THE BAND OF
7, AND MURDER CAME
SECOND-NATURE TO ME.
I'VE DONE SOME HORRIBLE THINGS.
MY DARK SIDE HAS KILLED SO MANY,
AND DURING IT ALL, THE DOCTOR IN
ME WAS HELPLESS TO STOP THE
SENSELESS BRUTALITY.
NO MATTER HOW MANY LIVES I
SAVED, NO MATTER HOW I TRIED TO
MAKE A DIFFERENCE, MY SOUL HAS
NO HOPE OF BEING REDEEMED.
>> DOCTOR SUIKOTSU, YOU ARE NOT
ALONE IN YOUR TURMOIL.
GOOD AND EVIL COEXIST IN ALL MEN
WHO WALK THE EARTH.
YOU MUST NOT GIVE IN TO THE DARK
SIDE.
>> YOU ARE WRONG, LADY KIKYO.
I WOULD LIKELY DO IT ALL AGAIN
IF I WERE ABLE TO.
I COULDN'T STOP MYSELF.
THE MERE THOUGHT OF IT IS
UNBEARABLE.
PLEASE, I BEG OF YOU,
LADY KIKYO...
REMOVE THE JEWEL SHARD.
GIVE ME DEATH AND RELEASE MY
TORMENTED SOUL.
>> DOCTOR SUIKOTSU.
>> PLEASE DO THIS FOR ME.
I BEG OF YOU.
>> [SIGHS]
>> I KNOW ONE THING, KIKYO,
DEAD PEOPLE LIKE YOU AND I WILL
PROBABLY SHARE THE SAME FATE.
>> HUH?!
>> HUMPH.
I'LL TAKE THIS AS A MEMENTO.
>> DOCTOR SUIKOTSU.
>> AND SO IT ENDS.
IT'S FINALLY OVER.
>> [GASPS]
>> HA!
FAREWELL, LOSERS!
>> SUIKOTSU, MAY YOU REST IN
PEACE.
>> EXCUSE ME, PRIESTESS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR SAVING MY
LIFE.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE NOT HURT.
YOU MUST'VE BEEN SCARED.
>> MM-HMM.
AT TIMES, HE WAS FRIGHTENING,
BUT OTHER TIMES...
HUH?
GOODBYE!
>> I, TOO, MUST LEAVE THIS
PLACE BEFORE THE SOULS WITHIN
ME FADE AND I'M LEFT UNABLE
TO MOVE.
>> HMM.
THE PRIESTESS WHO BOUND
INUYASHA TO A TREE.
SHE'S JUST LIKE THE OTHERS,
REEKING OF BUMS AND GRAVEYARD
SOIL.
PERHAPS SHE WAS GIVEN A GLIMPSE
OF HER OWN FATE.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU?
>> WE MUST LEAVE, RIN.
>> COMING.
>> I WISH THEY WOULD LEAVE.
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT THEM.
>> KOHAKU.
>> [GASPS]
>> STOP THEM.
THEY MUSTN'T ESCAPE.
>> RIGHT.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> WE MUST'VE SPENT THE ENTIRE
NIGHT TRYING TO FIND OUR WAY OUT
OF THE CAVE.
>> I CAN'T SEEM TO FIGURE OUT
THAT APPARITION.
WHY WOULD'VE IT HAVE DONE THAT?
>> HUH?
THIS CAPE.
DON'T TELL ME.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS?
>> A CAPE MADE FROM
PHOSPHORESCENT MOSS.
DEMON SLAYERS USE IT FOR NIGHT
RAIDS.
KOHAKU WAS HERE.
>> SANGO?
>> WE MUST HURRY, MIROKU.
>> KOGA.
>> SAY SOMETHING.
>> YOU BETTER NOT DIE ON US,
KOGA.
>> I'VE SEEN LOTS OF STRANGE
THINGS, BUT WHAT IS HE THINKING?
>> [GRUNTS]
THE WEATHER IS TOO NICE
AROUND HERE.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> RENKOTSU HAS HIS EYES ON
KOGA'S SACRED JEWEL SHARDS IN
THE HOPES OF AVENGING GINKOTSU'S
DEATH.
>> THE RIVER IS COVERED WITH
OIL.
THERE'S NOWHERE FOR YOU TO RUN.
>> CAREFUL, HE HAS BOMBS WITH
HIM!
>> HE'S GOING TO BLOW UP THE
WHOLE PLACE, AND GET KILLED IN
THE PROCESS.
>> ONLY YOU PEOPLE WILL DIE.
I WILL SURVIVE.
>> OH, YEAH?
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
>> NEXT TIME, "VANISHED IN A
RIVER OF FLAMES."
>> DID THE MUTT GET BLOWN TO
BITS?