[BELLS RINGING;
CHATTERING]
- LATER!
- HOLD IT!
GET BACK HERE!
YOU'RE ON CLEANING DUTY!
- I KNOW, BUT I'VE
GOT TO MEET SOMEONE.
I PROMISE, I'LL
MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
- DON'T TELL ME--YOU'RE
GOING TO SEE YOUR BOYFRIEND.
- SHE WOULDN'T, WOULD SHE?
- I TOLD YOU ALREADY!
I DO NOT HAVE A BOYFRIEND!
GOOD-BYE.
I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
OH!
- UH...
- IT HITS ALL
THE PRESSURE POINTS.
CAN'T HURT TO TRY IT.
- UH, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
- GOT TO GIVE HIM POINTS
FOR BEING PERSISTENT.
- HE MIGHT HAVE
BETTER LUCK WITH FLOWERS.
- MM-HMM.
- I KNOW SITTING BOTHERS YOU,
BUT DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
MAKE IT THROUGH A MOVIE?
IT'S JUST 2 HOURS.
- UH...
- HUDDLE!
- WAIT A SEC.
DID HE JUST ASK ME
ON A DATE?
- THAT'S WHAT
IT LOOKED LIKE TO ME.
- WHY DON'T YOU GO?
- YOU'D BE THE ENVY
OF ALL THE GIRLS,
ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING
IT'S YOUR FIRST DATE.
- UH...
- GET REAL!
YOU MEAN YOU'VE NEVER, EVER
BEEN ON A DATE BEFORE?
- COME ON!
GIVE ME A BREAK HERE!
OF COURSE I HAVE!
NOT.
THE MOVIES, HUH?
SURE. I GUESS
WE COULD GO TOGETHER.
- HEY, THAT'S GREAT.
SEE YOU SATURDAY.
I'LL SWING BY YOUR PLACE
AT HALF PAST 6:00.
- HUH?
HALF PAST!
OH, NO!
THE PAST IS THE PROBLEM!
WHAT IF I DON'T
GET BACK IN TIME?
I'LL MISS MY VERY FIRST DATE!
INUYASHA, WHAT DO YOU
THINK THE CHANCES ARE
OF GETTING BACK
BY SATURDAY?
- UH, FAIR TO MODERATE,
IF WE'RE LUCKY.
- OH, GREAT.
- WHEN EXACTLY WAS THIS
SATURDAY OF YOURS AGAIN?
- OH...I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
- HMM!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- WOW!
THIS IS AWESOME!
LOOK! A FISH!
- YOU MIND FOCUSING A LITTLE?
WE'RE NOT HERE
TO LOOK AT THE SCENERY.
- AYE-AYE, MON CAPITAN.
ON THE LOOKOUT FOR SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL!
[GROANING]
- SHIPPO, YOU CALL
YOURSELF A DEMON?
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO GET SEASICK.
- I'M NOT TRYING.
- THIS IS PATHETIC.
- WE'RE NOT GOING
TO FIND ANY SHARDS
UNLESS YOU TWO SNAP TO IT.
HMM?
- WHAT IS IT?
- SPIDERWEBS.
- THOSE ARE SPIDERWEBS?
ARE YOU SURE?
- HUH. HMM.
- MASTER INUYASHA,
WHAT MANNER OF WEBS ARE THEY?
- NOTHING TO BE
CONCERNED ABOUT.
HUH?
- UP THERE!
- KEEP AWAY FROM ME!
AAH!
- GOOD CATCH, INUYASHA!
- LOOKS LIKE
SOME TYPE OF DEMON.
- MY THANKS. YOU SAVED ME
FROM CERTAIN DEATH.
OH!
- HUH?
- DEMON! UNHAND ME!
- AAH!
- THINK OF THIS AS PRESERVED
HERBS FOR AILMENTS.
[GRUMBLING]
- DO YOU MIND MY ASKING
WHAT WAS AFTER YOU JUST NOW?
- A DEMON KNOWN AS
A SPIDER HEAD.
THESE MOUNTAINS
HAVE BEEN PLAGUED
BY THEIR EVIL PRESENCE
SINCE SPRINGTIME.
SEVERAL VILLAGES HAVE
ALREADY BEEN ATTACKED.
SPIDER HEADS TRAP HUMANS
IN THEIR WEBS,
PARALYZE THEM,
AND DEVOUR THEM ALIVE.
THEY ARE TERRIFYING DEMONS.
- YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
- HEY, INUYASHA, WE HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING TO HELP.
- ANY SIGN OF THE SACRED
JEWEL FRAGMENTS?
- NOT YET, AND I DIDN'T
PICK UP ANYTHING
FROM THE SPIDER HEAD
JUST NOW.
- THEN LET'S MOVE OUT.
I WANT TO CROSS THESE
MOUNTAINS BEFORE NIGHTFALL.
- WE CAN'T JUST WALK AWAY!
THERE'S A DEMON ON THE LOOSE!
- LISTEN, I DON'T GO
SLAYING DEMONS
EVERY TIME A HUMAN COMES
RUNNING SCARED TO ME.
- NO ONE'S SUGGESTING YOU DO.
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO HIM?
USUALLY, HE'D AT LEAST
CHECK THINGS OUT.
- I'M LEAVING.
BEING OBLIGED TO A DEMON
DOES NOT SIT WELL WITH ME.
- FEIGNING SOME MEASURE
OF GRATITUDE
MIGHT SIT BETTER
WITH US, THOUGH.
- INSOLENT BEAST!
THANK YOU FOR REMINDING ME
WHY I DETEST DEMONS.
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
[THUD]
- HOW ABOUT DISPLAYING SOME
OF THAT OLD-FASHIONED CHIVALRY?
THAT MUST BE THE TEMPLE.
SEE? THAT WASN'T
SO BAD, WAS IT?
- HMM!
- YOU HAVE RETURNED.
ARE YOU INJURED, NAZUNA?
- OH, MASTER!
- OH, I FEARED THAT A SPIDER
HEAD MAY HAVE ATTACKED YOU.
- IT SPIED ME WHILE I ATTENDED
TO THE GRAVE SITES.
I HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO RELY ON
THESE DEMONS TO BRING ME HOME.
I'M SORRY, MASTER.
- ALL DEMONS ARE NOT
CREATED EQUAL, YOU KNOW.
- I DON'T SUPPOSE THEY ARE.
- OH, MAN. DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE LEAVING ANYWAY.
- WAIT, FRIENDS!
YOU MUST STAY THE NIGHT
HERE WITH US AT THE TEMPLE.
- NO, MASTER!
- GO. PREPARE A MEAL
FOR YOUR KIND GUESTS.
- YES.
- I BEG YOU DO FORGIVE
NAZUNA FOR HER RUDENESS.
HER PARENTS WERE
KILLED BY A SPIDER HEAD,
AND SHE HAS HARBORED
AN UNDERSTANDABLE FEAR
OF DEMONS SINCE THE INCIDENT.
I HAVE ATTEMPTED TO QUELL
HER FEARS BUT TO NO AVAIL.
- SO, WE PROBABLY WON'T RUN INTO
ONE OF THOSE SPIDER HEADS
ON OUR WAY THROUGH
THE MOUNTAINS, WILL WE?
- AS THE NUMBER OF MEN
DYING IN WARS INCREASES,
SO DO THE NUMBER
OF SPIDER HEADS...
BY LEAPS AND BOUNDS.
- LEAPS AND...
SAY, HOW ABOUT WE
TAKE HIM UP ON HIS OFFER?
- UH, WE'RE ON A QUEST,
AND I REFUSE TO ALLOW
SOME MEASLY SPIDERS
TO STOP US.
- STAY THE NIGHT WITH US
AND REST WITH EASE.
I HAVE POSTED SUTRAS
THROUGHOUT THE TEMPLE
TO WARD OFF ANY DEMONS
FROM ATTACKING US.
- UH...WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- SUPPOSE THERE'S
NO SENSE ARGUING.
[GIGGLES]
- AHH! WHAT A DELICIOUS MEAL.
PERHAPS WE SHOULD STAY
A FEW DAYS AND GET
TO KNOW NAZUNA BETTER.
- FUNNY HOW A COUPLE
BOWLS OF RICE CAN CHANGE
YOUR TUNE ABOUT SOMEONE.
- I LIKED HER FROM THE START.
I MERELY THOUGHT
SHE WAS LACKING IN MANNERS.
- IT'S GETTING LATE.
- HEY, INUYASHA?
- HMM?
- WHY THE LONG FACE?
- HMMPH. IT'S NOTHING.
WHAT?
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM?
- WAIT A SECOND.
I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
- HMM?
- YOU'RE AFRAID OF SPIDERS!
- WHOA! WHO'S AFRAID
OF THE BIG, BAD SPIDER?
OH!
- I'LL TAKE THAT AS A YES.
- I'M NOT AFRAID OF SPIDERS!
- NOW WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- TO GET SOME FRESH AIR!
I'M SLEEPING
OUTSIDE TONIGHT.
HUH?
DAMN! WE'RE SURROUNDED.
HOW COULD I HAVE MISSED
THEIR SCENT?
- AAH! SPIDER HEADS!
AAH!
- LOOK OUT!
THEY'RE BEHIND US, TOO!
- THEIR NUMBERS ARE GREAT,
BUT THEY ARE NOT
A FORMIDABLE ENEMY.
UP FOR SOME AFTER-DINNER
EXERCISE, MASTER?
- OH, YEAH.
WARD THEM OFF.
SO MUCH FOR
THE OLD PRIEST'S SUTRAS.
- MASTER!
MASTER!
THE SPIDER HEADS! OH!
THEY'VE GOT YOU!
- AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- MAKE A BREAK!
I'LL BE RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- BUT WE CAN'T--
- DO WHAT I SAY!
I CAN HANDLE THESE DEMONS.
HYAH!
- WHY'S HE ACTING
SO STRANGE TODAY?
- AND WHY ISN'T
THE TETSUSAIGA TRANSFORMING?
- AAH! AAH!
- FOX FIRE!
- I'VE GOT YOU!
- WE'VE GOT TO ESCAPE!
- NAZUNA! THE DEMONS HAVE
BROKEN THROUGH MY SEALS.
MY SUTRAS ARE
NO LONGER STRONG ENOUGH
TO WARD OFF THE SPIDER HEADS.
- OH, MASTER!
MASTER, NO!
[PANTING]
- WE SHOULD BE SAFE HERE.
[SIGHS]
- DAMN IT.
- WHAT'S WITH YOU?
YOU'RE ACTING
WEIRDER THAN NORMAL.
- LEAVE ME ALONE!
[KAGOME GASPS]
- WHAT HAS GOTTEN INTO YOU?
HUH?
- FORGET ABOUT ME FOR NOW.
YOU SHOULD BE MORE WORRIED
ABOUT YOURSELVES.
- YOUR HAIR'S GONE BLACK.
[SIGHS]
- IF YOU THINK YOU CAN
RELY ON MY STRENGTH
TO SAVE YOU THIS TIME,
YOU'D BETTER THINK AGAIN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- INUYASHA?
IS THAT YOU?
- NO. I'M A TALKING PUPPET.
- UGH!
HIS DOG EARS ARE GONE.
- YOU'RE NOT HALF DEMON ANYMORE.
YOU'RE HUMAN!
- YOU'RE LUCKY MY FANGS
AND CLAWS ARE GONE.
- ALL RIGHT. HOW ABOUT
TELLING US WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ALL HALF-DEMONS,
SUCH AS MASTER INUYASHA,
ARE SUBJECT TO CERTAIN
TIMES WHEN THEY LOSE
THEIR SUPERNATURAL
POWERS AS DEMONS.
- I DON'T REALLY FOLLOW YOU.
- FROM TIME TO TIME, HALF-DEMONS
ARE RENDERED NO STRONGER
THAN YOURSELF
OR ANY OTHER MERE MORTAL.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
FOR HIM, THE TIME MUST FALL
ON THE FIRST NIGHT
OF THE NEW CYCLE,
WHEN THE MOON IS DARK.
- OK. NOW I GET IT.
YOU MEAN, AT THE START
OF EACH MONTH
WHEN THE MOON ISN'T VISIBLE,
A NIGHT SUCH AS TONIGHT.
- PRECISELY.
- WHY, MASTER?
WHY DID YOU NOT INFORM US
THAT YOUR PERIOD OF
VULNERABILITY WAS IMPENDING?
- BECAUSE IF I HAD, YOU WOULD
HAVE TAKEN OFF A LONG TIME AGO.
- UH...OH?
HMM. HAVE YOU NOT
A WHIT OF TRUST IN ME?
- YEAH, I TRUST YOU TO RUN AWAY
WHEN THERE'S TROUBLE!
- THEN WHAT?
YOU CAN'T RELY ON ME, EITHER?
IF YOU TOLD ME THAT YOU'D
BE LOSING YOUR POWERS,
I NEVER WOULD HAVE
INSISTED THAT WE STAY
IN THE TEMPLE WITH NAZUNA!
SO MUCH FOR BEING ABLE
TO LEAN ON YOUR CLOSE FRIENDS!
- I DON'T TRUST
ANYBODY, GOT IT?
[GASPS]
- HUH. IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
IT'S JUST THE WAY
I'VE LIVED UNTIL NOW.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY I KNOW
HOW TO PROTECT MYSELF.
- INUYASHA, I HEAR
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
I JUST WISH YOU'D OPEN UP
TO ME MORE, AS YOUR FRIEND.
[SOBBING]
- HUH?
NO, WAIT. I'M THE ONE
WHO'S SUPPOSED TO BE DOWN.
- IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOUR PRIDE,
WE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS BOAT.
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY
FOR THIS BIG TIME, PAL!
GRAB A BRAIN, WOULD YOU?
YOU DOUGH HEAD!
- YOU'RE THE DOUGH HEAD!
- YOU COULD HAVE SAID NO
TO STAYING AT THE TEMPLE!
- NOW THAT INUYASHA'S BEEN
RENDERED A MERE MORTAL,
I SHALL HAVE TO TAKE OVER
PROTECTING THE OTHERS.
I'LL HAVE TO SUMMON
ALL MY COURAGE.
[RUSTLING LEAVES]
AAH!
SOMEONE SAVE ME!
- NAZUNA!
- I KNEW THAT.
- YOU MADE IT OUT OF THERE.
[PANTING]
- PLEASE, YOU MUST RETURN
AND AID THE PRIEST.
- WHAT?
YOU WANT US TO GO BACK?
- YOUR DEMON IS STRONG.
I'M CERTAIN HE CAN ASSIST US.
- HUH.
NOW, WHAT WERE YOU
SAYING ABOUT
NOT WANTING TO BE
OBLIGED TO DEMONS?
GET THE PRIEST TO WRITE UP
SOME MORE OF THOSE SUTRAS.
- YOUR COUNTENANCE
SEEMED ALTERED.
HAS YOUR HAIR NOT CHANGED?
- HUH. IT ISN'T EASY
BEING HUMAN. BELIEVE ME.
- AAH!
- OH, NO!
WHAT IS IT NOW?
- MY BAG! I FORGOT IT!
- SO GET A NEW ONE
WHEN YOU GO BACK.
- THING IS...
THE JEWEL SHARDS ARE INSIDE.
- WHAT?!
- UH...I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
- TAKE THIS.
- YOU AND NAZUNA STAY HERE
AND DON'T THINK ABOUT MOVING.
THE TETSUSAIGA WON'T
TRANSFORM FOR ME TONIGHT,
BUT I'LL BE ABLE TO HANDLE A FEW
SPIDER HEADS ON MY OWN STRENGTH.
- YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- IT'S TIME TO GO BACK
TO THE TEMPLE, SHIPPO.
LET'S MOVE.
- UH...
WHY DO YOU NEED ME?
[GRUNTING]
I AM STRONG ENOUGH
TO HANDLE THIS.
[GRUNTING]
I HAVE GOT TO BE STRONG.
[CHUCKLING]
- AAH! AAH!
[SHATTERING]
- HANDS OFF!
SO, YOU WERE PLANNING THIS
RIGHT FROM THE START.
[CHUCKLING]
- I COULD HARDLY CONTAIN
MYSELF WHEN I SAW YOU,
THE HALF-DEMON RUMORED
TO POSSESS JEWEL SHARDS!
[GRUNTING]
- THE JEWEL SHARDS!
HE SWALLOWED SOME OF THEM!
- WHAT AN UNFORTUNATE MISHAP
THAT YOUR SUPERHUMAN POWERS
HAVE DESERTED YOU.
BY THE TIME I TIE THE FINAL KNOT
ON MY GAUZY WEB OF DECEIT--
- I MAY NOT HAVE
MY USUAL POWERS...
[GRUNTING]
BUT I'LL STILL CRUSH YOU!
- FOX FIRE!
OH!
- FINALLY THIS TIRESOME CHARADE
AS A HUMAN HAS ENDED!
[COWERING]
AAH!
[MOANING]
- AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- NOW TELL ME
WHERE YOU HAVE HIDDEN
THE REMAINING SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL!
- OVER THERE!
- I BELIEVE YOU POSSESS THEM.
- MASTER!
I--I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
- HE WAS DECEIVING YOU.
- KAGOME!
INUYASHA'S BEEN POISONED.
- HOLD ON! I'M COMING!
- HUH?
- THE TETSUSAIGA IS PROTECTING
YOU AS IT DID BEFORE.
- SEEING YOU HERE
MUST MEAN WE HAVE
A GOOD CHANCE
AT WINNING THIS BATTLE.
OTHERWISE, YOU'D BE LONG GONE.
- I'M NOT CERTAIN
I APPROVE OF THE INSINUATION.
[CHUCKLES]
- I HAVE INJECTED A LARGE
QUANTITY OF POISON IN HIM.
HIS INNARDS WILL ALREADY
BE STARTING TO LIQUEFY.
- MASTER!
HOW CAN YOU DO THIS?
- KAGOME...SAVE YOURSELF.
- NO CHANCE.
- I'M SERIOUS.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR ME.
- I'M NOT LEAVING HERE
WITHOUT YOU.
NO...WAY!
[GRUNTS]
- HUH?
UGH!
- WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- THERE'S GOT TO BE
ANOTHER WAY.
- THERE IS A SMALL ROOM
AT THE END OF THE HALL.
QUICKLY!
- YOU CANNOT FLEE!
[GRUNTING]
- KAGOME, THRUST
THE TETSUSAIGA INTO THE DOOR.
QUICKLY!
- AAH! YOU WRETCHES!
- THE TETSUSAIGA
SHOULD BE POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO WARD THEM OFF
FOR SOME TIME.
- HE'S FREEZING!
INUYASHA, YOU HAVE
TO STAY WITH US!
SAY SOMETHING!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- THIS ALL HAPPENED,
BECAUSE I SUGGESTED
WE STAY HERE AT THE TEMPLE.
- YOU MUSTN'T PUT
THE BLAME ON YOURSELF.
- BUT IT IS ALL MY FAULT!
- I SHALL DRAW
THE POISON FROM HIS BLOOD.
[SUCKING]
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M MYOGA.
ALWAYS A BEAST,
NEVER A BURDEN.
OH...
[INUYASHA MOANS]
MASTER INUYASHA'S
SURVIVAL WILL DEPEND ON
HIS OWN STRENGTH
FROM THIS POINT.
[BURPS]
[LABORED BREATHING]
- HE'S DRIPPING IN SWEAT.
OH.
[MOANING]
- HUH?
- SORRY.
I DIDN'T
WAKE YOU UP, DID I?
- NO.
KAGOME.
- WHAT IS IT?
- TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHY WERE YOU CRYING?
- UH...
BACK IN THE OTHER ROOM?
BECAUSE...I THOUGHT
I WAS GOING TO LOSE YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING TO...DIE.
- YOU SHED TEARS FOR ME...
CRIED FOR ME.
KAGOME, IF IT'S NOT
TOO MUCH TROUBLE,
MAY I LIE ON YOUR LAP?
- HUH?
MMM.
[SIGHING]
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
A LITTLE BETTER THAN BEFORE?
- YES.
KAGOME...YOU SMELL
KIND OF NICE.
- HUH?
OK, THAT'S IT.
YOU MADE A POINT
OF TELLING ME BEFORE
THAT YOU COULDN'T
STAND MY SCENT.
- I DID...BUT I WAS LYING.
- MAYBE THIS POISON
REALLY HAS GONE TO HIS HEAD.
YET...ALL THIS TALK
HAS MY HEART POUNDING.
OK, NOW I'M CONFUSED.
[SNORES]
HE'S ASLEEP.
[RATTLING]
WHAT?
- AAH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- THE PRIEST MUST BE
IN PURSUIT AGAIN.
GET THE MASTER OUT OF HERE!
- WE'LL HAVE TO CARRY HIM.
HE'S UNCONSCIOUS.
- AAH!
[GROWLS]
[SCREAMING]
- WHOA!
- SHIPPO!
- I MUST POSSESS
THE REMAINING JEWEL FRAGMENTS!
- WHOA!
[SWALLOWING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRIMACES]
[LAUGHS]
- HOW DARE YOU POSSESS
THE BODY OF MY DEAR MASTER!
- THERE NEVER
WAS ANY PRIEST HERE.
IT WAS ALL A TRAP
TO LURE THE HALF-DEMON
AND HIS JEWELS TO ME!
- YOU--YOU
SLAUGHTERED MY PARENTS
AND ALL THE OTHER VILLAGERS?
[LAUGHS]
- YOU SERVED ME WELL,
GULLIBLE FOOL!
- TREACHEROUS BEAST!
UGH! UGH!
AAH!
- YOUR FEARS OF THE SPIDER HEADS
ARE NOW OVER.
ONCE I'VE CONSUMED YOU,
YOU WILL BECOME PART OF ME!
- FORGIVE ME, FATHER.
I SHOULD NEVER HAVE
TRUSTED THIS MONSTER.
- YOU'RE PRETTY DETERMINED,
FOR A HUMAN, THAT IS.
- YOU'RE ALIVE?
- INUYASHA!
[CACKLES]
INUYASHA!
- LOOK! THE SUN IS RISING!
- HUH?
- YOU'RE A FINE
HUMAN SPECIMEN.
- DON'T BE SO SURE ABOUT THAT.
- YOU'RE BEGINNING
TO TRANSFORM,
BUT I SHALL DEVOUR YOU
BEFOREHAND!
- IF THERE'S ONE THING
I CAN'T STAND,
IT'S AN ARROGANT SPIDER
THAT DOESN'T KNOW
WHEN TO KEEP ITS HANDS OFF!
THE MOONLESS NIGHT
HAS COME TO AN END!
- THE AAH! SWORD'S
REGAINED ITS POWER!
- YOU GOT IT, SPIDER HEAD!
AAH!
[CLANG]
- THE SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL!
THEY FUSED TOGETHER
INSIDE THE DEMON'S BODY!
- IS THAT ALL
WE HAVE SO FAR?
I THOUGHT WE HAD A LOT MORE.
- HEY, IT'S ENOUGH
TO IMPRESS THIS GIRL.
- THIS IS FAR ENOUGH.
THE VILLAGE IS CLOSE BY.
- OK.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
- OH, AND, INUYASHA,
I APPRECIATE YOUR HELP.
I'LL TRY TO REMEMBER THAT
SOME DEMONS AREN'T ALL BAD.
NOT MANY, BUT SOME.
- DON'T KID YOURSELF,
NAZUNA.
ALL DEMONS ARE BAD.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
- I WON'T FORGET YOU!
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE
IN MY PRAYERS, INUYASHA!
- HUH.
WHATEVER.
- HE SEEMS LIKE HIS OLD SELF.
- KAGOME...YOU SMELL
KIND OF NICE.
- DID HE ACTUALLY SAY THAT,
OR DID I HEAR WRONG?
HIS BODY IS TRANSFORMED, BUT
WHAT ABOUT HIS FEELINGS FOR ME?
SHOULD I ASK HIM?
- HUH? ARE YOU GOING
TO KEEP STARING AT ME?
BECAUSE IT'S TICKING ME OFF.
IF YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING
TO SAY, SAY IT!
- THEN AGAIN, SOME THINGS
ARE BETTER LEFT UNSAID.
[MOANING]
- ARE WE THERE YET?
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PULL OVER
FOR A SHORT REST?
- YEAH, SURE, AS SOON AS YOU
GET OVER YOUR SEASICKNESS.
- HEY, INUYASHA?
- HUH?
[SHIPPO THROWS UP]
OH!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- IN A BATTLE FOR THE SACRED
JEWEL 50 YEARS AGO,
INUYASHA WAS BOUND TO A TREE
BY KIKYO'S ARROW.
KIKYO, KAEDE'S SISTER,
WAS FATALLY INJURED
IN THE CONFRONTATION.
WE RETURNED FROM OUR JOURNEY
TO FIND KIKYO'S GRAVE SITE
DESECRATED!
WHO WAS IT THAT ROBBED
THE GRAVE, AND WHY?
SOMETHING TELLS ME THERE'S
GOING TO BE SERIOUS TROUBLE!
NEXT TIME,
"KIKYO'S STOLEN ASHES."
SEE YOU SOON!