>> PRINCESS ABI,
THE BIRD MASTER.
>> YES.
WHO ARE YOU?
>> MAKE ME A PATH SO I CAN
CROSS OVER.
>> HOW DARE YOU ORDER ME AROUND
LIKE THAT!
>> IT WASN'T INTENDED
AS AN ORDER.
IT'S A TRADE.
>> HMM.
>> AND I GUARANTEE YOU'LL HAVE
NO INTERRUPTIONS FROM ANYONE.
THAT IS MADE FROM MY BONES.
I SHALL LEND IT TO YOU.
>> OH.
[SCREECHING]
>> WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
>> HMM. HERE THEY COME.
WIND SCAR!
>> THERE'S MORE OF THEM COMING!
>> THEY'RE ON FIRE!
>> THEY'RE BURNING THE HOUSES
TO FORCE THE VILLAGERS OUTSIDE!
>> AAH!
>> [SHOUTS IN JAPANESE]
THEY'RE COMING BACK!
>> CURSE THEM!
WIND TUNNEL!
>> SIAMYOSHO!
>> UP THERE!
>> WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE,
AND WHY DO YOU INTERFERE
WITH ME?
>> SHUT UP.
ARE YOU ONE OF NARAKU'S MINIONS?
>> NARAKU?
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE IN TIGHT
WITH HIM.
THE SIAMYOSHO BUZZING AROUND YOU
ARE PROOF!
>> I DON'T KNOW HIM, NOR DO I
KNOW WHAT YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH THIS NARAKU IS, BUT YOU
MADE THE MISTAKE OF
SLAUGHTERING MY BIRDS.
I'LL KILL EACH ONE OF YOU AND
DRAIN EVERY LAST DROP OF YOUR
BLOOD.
YOU WILL DIE!
>> WATCH OUT!
YOU'RE DEAD.
>> AAH!
DAMN YOU!
>> INUYASHA!
>> CURSE YOU.
TAKE THIS!
>> WIND SCAR!
>> WHO IS THIS HALF DEMON?
HIS DEMONIC POWER IS GREATER
THAN I THOUGHT.
HA!
>> A BARRIER!
COME BACK HERE!
>> NARAKU IS TRYING TO FIND
A WAY TO GET TO THE BORDER
BETWEEN THIS LIFE AND THE NEXT
IN ORDER TO GET THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD.
>> SO YOU MEAN COLLECTING HUMAN
BLOOD IS SOMEHOW RELATED TO HIS
GETTING TO THE BORDER?
>> SEEMS LIKE IT.
WHATEVER THE CONNECTION IS,
IT'S THE ONLY THING WE HAVE TO
GO ON AT THIS POINT.
>> THE PATH THAT LEADS
TO THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS
WORLD AND THE NEXT.
IT WILL SOON OPEN.
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> DEMON BIRDS!
>> HAVE MERCY!
>> [GROWLS]
>> PAPA! MAMA!
>> DON'T CRY.
LET'S GO.
>> GO?
WHERE TO?
>> TO SEE THE HOLY ONE.
>> ARE YOU TWO LEAVING
AS WELL?
>> MM-HMM.
>> THEN LET'S TRAVEL TOGETHER.
COME ALONG WITH US.
>> DID THOSE DEMON BIRDS
DO THIS TO THE VILLAGERS?
>> YES.
I'M ALMOST CERTAIN OF IT.
>> THEY SEEM TO BE ATTACKING
EVERY VILLAGE AND HAMLET
IN THIS REGION.
>> I WONDER ABOUT THAT DEMON
WHO CALLS HERSELF PRINCESS ABI.
WHAT COULD HER PURPOSE BE?
>> SAY, INUYASHA, WHAT DO YOU
THINK SHE'S UP TO?
WHY WOULD SHE BE GATHERING
SO MUCH HUMAN BLOOD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> LET'S GO, EVERYONE.
>> HUH?
>> WE NEED TO FIND THE NEST.
>> NEST?
YOU MEAN THE NEST OF DEMON
BIRDS?
>> MM-HMM.
>> SANGO'S GOT A POINT.
BESIDES, WE'VE GOT NO OTHER
CLUES TO GO ON.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HMM.
>> ♪ MASTER JAKEN,
MASTER JAKEN,
WHY, OH, WHY ARE YOU SO GREEN? ♪
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> LOOKS LIKE WE'VE BEEN
LEFT BEHIND AGAIN.
BORING, ISN'T IT, MASTER JAKEN?
>> YOU SAID IT, BORING.
I COULD HAVE ACCOMPANIED LORD
SESSHOMARU IF I DIDN'T HAVE
TO BABY-SIT THIS CHILD.
HMM?
HMM.
>> [BOTH YELLING]
>> HUH?
AAH!
MASTER JAKEN!
>> KAGURA, YOU BACK AGAIN?
YOU'D BETTER NOT BE HERE
TO ABDUCT LITTLE RIN.
>> COME ON.
DID I EVER TRY AND ABDUCT HER?
>> OF COURSE!
DON'T DENY IT!
>> IS SESSHOMARU AROUND?
>> YOU FOOL, IF LORD SESSHOMARU
WERE HERE, YOUR WORTHLESS HEAD
WOULD BE ROLLING ON THE GROUND
BY NOW.
>> I GUESS IT WOULD.
>> HMM?
>> AAH!
>> SHE LEFT ALREADY.
>> HMM, WHAT DID SHE WANT
ANYWAY?
>> I SUPPOSE HE HAS A GOOD
POINT.
IF I CAME EMPTYHANDED TO
SESSHOMARU, I MIGHT AS WELL
EXPECT TO BE KILLED.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
DON'T PLAY WITH MY LIFE,
YOU BRAT!
[MOANING]
>> DOES IT HURT, KAGURA?
>> I WASN'T ABLE TO KILL THAT
BRAT HAKUDOSHI WITH MY DANCE OF
BLADES.
STILL, IN ORDER TO BECOME FREE,
I MUST KILL NARAKU
AND HAKUDOSHI.
HOLD IT.
THAT INFANT SPLIT APART
INTO TWO.
>> IT'S HIS FATE.
THIS WAS ALL MEANT TO HAPPEN.
>> IS THERE A PURPOSE FOR
THAT OTHER HALF, TOO?
>> THERE MUST BE.
>> AND I'M ALMOST CERTAIN IT'S
MORE IMPORTANT THAN HAKUDOSHI.
THAT'S WHY HE ENTRUSTED IT
TO KANNA.
HE TRUSTS HER MORE THAN ME.
THERE HAS TO BE A SECRET, MAYBE
EVEN SOMETHING THAT COULD PUT
AN END TO NARAKU'S LIFE.
[THUNDER]
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
WHY CAN I NOT HEAR THE BABY'S
FIRST CRIES?
PLEASE, CAN I HOLD HIM?
>> MY LADY, REGRETFULLY I HAVE
TO TELL YOU THE YOUNG LORD
WAS STILLBORN.
>> WHAT?
ARE YOU SAYING MY BABY IS DEAD?
>> YES.
HE WASN'T BREATHING WHEN HE WAS
BORN.
>> THIS CAN'T BE!
[SOBBING]
>> MY LADY, I'M SO SORRY.
>> THE INFANT IS NOT DEAD.
THE CHILD IS HERE.
>> DAMN IT ALL.
>> THIS IS SO FRUSTRATING.
NOT A SINGLE CLUE YET.
>> YOU'D THINK DEMON BIRDS
WOULD NEST UP HIGH, BUT WE
HAVEN'T FOUND ANYTHING.
>> PRINCESS ABI HAS NARAKU
PROTECTING HER.
MAYBE THE NEST IS HIDDEN BEHIND
A BARRIER.
>> I'LL GLADLY RIP THROUGH
ANY DAMN BARRIER OF HIS.
>> SOUNDS GOOD EXCEPT FOR
THE PART WHERE WE HAVE TO FIND
THE BARRIER FIRST.
>> SHUT UP.
I KNOW THAT.
THIS IS SO NOT FUNNY.
IT'S LIKE NARAKU'S LEADING US
AROUND BY THE NOSE.
>> INUYASHA, UP THERE!
>> I CAN'T GO ANY FURTHER.
YOU GO ON WITHOUT ME.
>> YOU CAN DO IT.
>> YOU ESCAPED FROM THE VILLAGE?
>> YES.
IT WAS SO FRIGHTENING.
WE NEVER KNEW WHEN THE DEMON
BIRDS WOULD ATTACK NEXT.
EVERYONE IN THE REGION IS
PACKING UP AND LEAVING.
>> YOU PEOPLE ARE A GODSEND.
>> IT ALWAYS ENDS UP LIKE THIS.
>> SO YOU SHOULD BE USED TO IT.
>> SO, WHAT NOW?
DO YOU HAVE A PLACE TO GO TO?
>> I BELIEVE SO.
WE PLAN TO APPEAL TO
ST. AGIRI, THE HOLY ONE.
IT'S OUT BEYOND THE PASS IN THE
MOUNTAINS, SO HOPEFULLY WE CAN
FIND REFUGE THERE FROM
THE DEMON BIRDS.
>> THE HOLY ONE?
>> IT THIS HOLY PERSON A PRIEST?
>> WELL, NO ONE KNOWS FOR SURE.
WE'VE ONLY HEARD RUMORS ABOUT
THE PERSON.
>> NO ONE HAS ACTUALLY SEEN
THE HOLY ONE.
>> WHAT?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
>> THE FACE IS ALWAYS HIDDEN,
AND NO ONE HAS EVER HEARD
THE GREAT ONE'S VOICE.
COMMUNICATION BETWEEN THE HOLY
ONE AND THE PEOPLE IS CONDUCTED
BY THE 2 ATTENDANTS.
SO NO ONE KNOWS WHETHER
THE PERSON IS OLD OR YOUNG
OR EVEN MALE OR FEMALE.
>> JEEZ, YOU'RE PLANNING THIS
WHOLE JOURNEY AROUND SOMEONE
YOU'VE ONLY HEARD RUMORS ABOUT?
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
DOES THIS MEAN ALL THE
VILLAGERS ARE GOING THERE BASED
ON NOTHING BUT THESE RUMORS?
>> YES.
>> COME ON, MIROKU.
I THINK WE'D BETTER HURRY UP.
>> I AGREE.
>> HURRY?
WHY IS THAT?
>> BECAUSE THE BIRDS SHOW UP
WHEREVER THERE ARE A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
KAGOME, GET ON.
>> THANK YOU FOR
CARRYING ME, YOUNG MONK.
>> I'LL PUT YOU DOWN AS SOON
AS WE REACH SAFETY.
>> EVERYONE, BEYOND
THIS PASS IS THE HOLY ONE'S
VILLAGE.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
>> HEY, HAKUDOSHI.
WHAT'S UP YOUR SLEEVE THIS TIME?
>> LOOK AT ALL THAT BIRD FOOD,
KAGURA.
>> HMM?
>> WE'LL TAKE EVERY LAST DROP
OF THEIR BLOOD TO CREATE
THE PATH BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE AFTERLIFE.
>> [NEIGHS]
>> HUH?
>> HERE THEY COME.
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> [SHOUTS IN JAPANESE]
HAH!
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> IT'S KAGURA'S
DANCE OF BLADES.
>> IT'S BEEN A WHILE, INUYASHA.
>> [ALL GASP]
>> HAKUDOSHI.
WHAT ARE YOU SHOWING
YOUR UGLY FACE HERE FOR?
>> OH, COME NOW.
WHILE YOU BABBLE ON LIKE THAT,
INNOCENT HUMANS WILL DIE.
>> [YELLING]
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> STAY TOGETHER.
DON'T SCATTER AROUND.
>> OK.
>> TAKE THIS.
WIND SCAR!
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> HE DID IT!
>> WHERE DO ALL THESE DEMON
BIRDS KEEP COMING FROM?
>> THIS IS NO GOOD.
AS LONG AS WE'RE BUSY
PROTECTING THE VILLAGERS, WE'RE
NOT FREE TO DO ANYTHING ELSE.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE
ABOUT THIS.
>> I KNOW.
HAKUDOSHI AND KAGURA ARE MERELY
WATCHING.
THEY'RE NOT EVEN GETTING
INVOLVED.
AND LOOK AT THE BIRDS.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF THEY'RE
MERELY TRYING TO BUY TIME.
OH, NO!
>> THAT'S RIGHT!
I BET THERE ARE WAY MORE PEOPLE
AT THE HOLY ONE'S VILLAGE THAN
THERE ARE HERE.
>> [GRUNTS]
>> [CHUCKLES]
YOU FIGURED IT OUT.
IT'S TOO LATE NOW, THOUGH.
BY THIS TIME, PRINCESS ABI AND
HER MAIN FORCE OF DEMON BIRDS
HAVE BEGUN THEIR ATTACK ON THE
SO-CALLED HOLY ONE'S VILLAGE.
>> THEN IT WAS YOU WHO WAS
SPREADING THESE RUMORS ABOUT
THIS HOLY ONE.
>> HA HA HA.
I COULDN'T HAVE BEEN BOTHERED.
IT'S ONLY A HOLY PERSON,
PROBABLY JUST ANOTHER
RUN-OF-THE-MILL EXORCIST.
BECAUSE THE VILLAGERS WERE
SO AFRAID OF THE DEMON BIRDS,
THEY RAISED THE SPIRITUAL ONE
TO GODLY STATUS.
WE LEARNED ABOUT THIS DIVINE
ONE, AND WE CAME TO MEET HIM.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
>> HOW DARE YOU, BASTARD!
>> COUNTERING YOUR WIND SCAR
TAKES NO EFFORT,
NOT FOR ME.
>> DAMN YOU.
>> MASTER, I CAN SEE THEM.
THE SAME DEMON BIRDS ARE
ATTACKING THE VILLAGE.
>> STOP YOUR RESISTANCE
AND OBSERVE AS THE FOOLISH
HUMANS ARE REDUCED
TO DEMON BIRD FODDER.
>> [ALL GASP]
>> HA!
YOUR BARRIER AIN'T THAT STRONG.
I'LL BUST RIGHT THROUGH
THE THING!
>> IT'S THE RED TETSUSAIGA
THAT BREAKS THROUGH BARRIERS.
>> HE DID IT.
>> WHA--?
>> NO, IT CAN'T BE.
>> THE RED TETSUSAIGA
DIDN'T WORK?
>> SO, EVEN INUYASHA CAN'T
BREAK THOUGH?
DAMN!
CURSE YOU, HAKUDOSHI.
WHAT DOES IT TAKE TO KILL YOU?
>> HA HA HA.
AAH!
WHO FIRED THAT ARROW?
>> [ALL GASP]
>> THE BARRIER IS GONE.
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
ISN'T THAT--?
>> WIND SCAR!
>> INUYASHA!
>> HE GOT HIM!
>> IT'S OVER NOW.
AAH!
WHAT THE...?
>> KAGURA, TIME TO GO.
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
YAH!
TOO FAST.
LET ME HANDLE THEM.
GET OUT OF HERE.
>> RIGHT.
>> THIS WAY, EVERYONE.
>> HURRY.
>> INUYASHA!
>> KILALA!
DAMN YOU!
KILALA!
>> IT'S NOT WORKING.
THAT DEMON HORSE IS TOO FAST.
>> DAMN.
THAT HORSE IS SO FAST.
EVEN IF WE MEET HEAD ON, ALL
I CAN DO IS COUNTER HIS MOVES.
MIGHT AS WELL GIVE IT A TRY.
KILALA, OVER THERE.
THAT'S IT.
FOLLOW ME IN.
HA!
END OF THE ROAD,
YOU DAMNED HORSE.
YOU MOVE WITH LIGHTNING
SPEED, I'LL GIVE YOU THAT,
BUT THIS CAVE IS TOO SMALL
FOR YOU TO MANEUVER IN.
HA! THAT'S THE WAY.
[GRUNTS]
JUST WHAT I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR.
NOW, BACKLASH WAVE!
>> [GROWLING]
>> INUYASHA!
HUH?
THAT WAS THE SACRED ARROW
THAT BROKE THROUGH
HAKUDOSHI'S BARRIER.
>> THIS ARROW--IT CAME
FROM THAT DIRECTION,
BUT NO ONE'S THERE.
>> [MUSIC]
>> NARAKU'S DEMONS!
>> IT'S AS THOUGH THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR SOMETHING.
>> ARE THEY SEARCHING
FOR THE HOLY ONE?
PRINCESS ABI'S HUGE ARMY OF
BIRDS WAS DESTROYED WITH
A SINGLE ARROW.
>> AND IT BROKE THROUGH
HAKUDOSHI'S BARRIER.
>> HAS NARAKU FOUND OUT THAT
THIS HOLY PERSON MIGHT BE KIKYO?
IS HE GOING TO TRY TO KILL HER
AGAIN?
>> HE'LL DO SOMETHING.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> NEXT TIME: "THE MYSTERIOUS
LIGHT THAT GUIDES THE SAINT."
>> SOUL COLLECTORS?
IS KIKYO REALLY ALIVE?