- IS THAT ALL THE POWER
YOU CAN MUSTER?
- I SEE YOU FOUND
ANOTHER UGLY ARM FOR ME
TO CHOP OFF, SESSHOMARU.
- GO AHEAD AND TRY IT.
THIS REPLACEMENT ARM WILL ACT AS
A SHIELD AGAINST THE TETSUSAIGA.
- THAT'S A DRAGON'S CLAW.
- HUH?
- A DRAGON'S CLAW WILL
HAVE A GREAT DEAL MORE POWER
THAN A TYPICAL DEMON'S.
I WONDER HOW HE'S GONNA
USE THAT THING IN BATTLE.
- HMPH. DRAGON'S CLAW. WHATEVER.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE IT'S GONNA
DO ANY BETTER THAN THE LAST ARM.
I'VE ALREADY TAKEN A GOOD CHUNK
OUT OF IT WITH MY SWORD.
- THE TETSUSAIGA IS AMAZING.
DESPITE NOT BEING WIELDED
BY ITS TRUE OWNER,
ITS POWER IS STILL FORMIDABLE.
HOWEVER, IT REFUSES
TO REVEAL THE WIND SCAR
TO THE ONE IT HAS RECEIVED
AS ITS MASTER.
TETSUSAIGA,
CUT THROUGH THE EMPTINESS
AND REVEAL YOUR POWER.
- D'AH!
SESSHOMARU MUST BE ABLE
TO SEE THE WIND SCAR.
- THE WIND SCAR? WHAT IS THAT?
- IN A NUTSHELL, THE WIND SCAR
IS THE SECRET TO TETSUSAIGA'S
ULTIMATE POWER.
SLAYING 100 DEMONS IN ONE SWEEP
WOULD BE VIRTUALLY IMPOSSIBLE
UNLESS YOU CAN SEE
THE WIND SCAR.
SESSHOMARU MUST BE
ABLE TO SEE IT.
- WELL, IF SESSHOMARU
CAN SEE IT,
CAN'T YOU TEACH INUYASHA
TO SEE IT, TOO?
- IT IS IMPOSSIBLE TO TEACH.
INUYASHA MUST DISCOVER IT
WITHIN HIMSELF,
AND IF HE DOES NOT
DISCOVER IT IN TIME,
THEN HE WILL SURELY DIE.
- AAH!
[SWORD HUMMING]
RRGH. DAMN.
ALL HE'S USING AGAINST ME
IS THE CLAW'S BRUTE STRENGTH.
[ALL GASP]
- INUYASHA!
[SWORD HUMMING]
- I THINK THE SWORD IS CRYING.
- FROM WHAT I CAN SEE,
SESSHOMARU IS ACTUALLY
ATTACKING THE SWORD ITSELF.
- THIS IS APPALLING.
HE KEEPS HACKING AWAY
AT THE SWORD,
SENDING MIGHTY WAVES OF POWER
RINGING THROUGHOUT THE BLADE.
EVEN THE GREAT TETSUSAIGA
WILL BREAK UNDER THIS PRESSURE.
- SESSHOMARU
ISN'T FIGHTING WITH ME.
HE'S FIGHTING WITH TETSUSAIGA.
GAAH!
UH! UNGH!
- INUYASHA!
- STAY BACK!
- HUH?
- DON'T INTERFERE.
I WILL KILL SESSHOMARU,
AND I'LL DO IT
WITH THE TETSUSAIGA.
HE'S HITTING TETSUSAIGA
OVER AND OVER AGAIN
TO TRY TO BREAK IT,
AS IF I'M GONNA STAND BY
AND LET HIM DO THAT.
- WE HAVE TO REMEMBER
THAT INUYASHA
HAS TAPPED INTO THE TETSUSAIGA'S
FULL STRENGTH BEFORE.
I KNOW IT WAS ONLY ONCE,
BUT IT PROVED THAT HE'S CAPABLE
OF DOING IT AGAIN.
- WELL, INUYASHA BETTER
TAP INTO IT REAL SOON,
OR HE'S GONNA END UP DEAD.
BE CAREFUL.
- WHY WON'T YOU ROAR,
TETSUSAIGA?
THEN YOU CAN DIE
ALONG WITH YOUR WEAK MASTER.
- HRRAAAGH!
- YOU...
YOU'RE PROTECTING YOUR SWORD.
- UGH. HA!
WHY WOULD I LET YOU
BUST UP THE TETSUSAIGA
BEFORE I'VE LEARNED
HOW TO CONTROL IT?
AAH!
AAAH! AAH! UHH!
UH!
[PANTING]
DAMN IT ALL. I CAN'T SEE.
HUH?
I CAN SENSE IT...
THE VORTEX OF HIS POWER.
I CAN SMELL THE WIND SCRAPING.
IT'S AGAINST THE FISSURE
WHERE THE POWER FLOWS THROUGH.
I BET I CAN SLICE
THROUGH THE FISSURE
AND RELEASE THE POWER.
I SEE IT.
- UGH! AAH!
UGH! AAH!
[GROANING]
- [GRUNTING]
HUH?
[PANTING]
IS IT OVER?
SO THAT'S THE WIND SCAR.
- YOU DID IT, INUYASHA.
YOU DISCOVERED
TETSUSAIGA'S SECRET,
AND NOW YOU CAN MASTER IT.
- SO DOES THAT MEAN
SESSHOMARU IS DEAD?
- MOST LIKELY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
HE COULD'VE SURVIVED.
HE RECEIVED A DIRECT BLOW
FROM THE FULLY EMPOWERED
TETSUSAIGA.
- I DIDN'T SEE INUYASHA
MAKE A DIRECT BLOW.
ALL HE DID WAS WILDLY
SWING HIS SWORD AROUND
BECAUSE HIS EYES
WERE BLINDED WITH POISON.
- WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
- HMPH. LISTEN, INUYASHA.
YOU DISCOVERED THE WIND SCAR--
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT MUCH--
BUT ALL IT MEANS IS THAT YOU NOW
KNOW WHAT YOUR BROTHER KNOWS.
YOU'RE STILL NOT HIS EQUAL,
AND NOW HE IS
EVEN MORE FORMIDABLE
THAN HE WAS BEFORE.
- YOU REFER TO HIM
AS THOUGH HE WERE STILL ALIVE.
- SESSHOMARU IS STILL ALIVE,
AND EVEN THOUGH
HE DESPISES THE TENSEIGA,
IT PROTECTED HIS LIFE.
- IT PROTECTED HIS LIFE?
- DO YOU MEAN SESSHOMARU
IS STILL AROUND SOMEWHERE?
- INUYASHA, WHEN YOU
USED THE WIND SCAR
AGAINST SESSHOMARU,
YOU DIDN'T FEEL IT
STRIKE HIM, DID YOU?
- IS THAT TRUE, INUYASHA?
- UH, HARD TO SAY.
I WAS BLINDED.
HIS BODY FELT LIKE IT
DISINTEGRATED IN THE BLAST
FROM THE TETSUSAIGA.
I DIDN'T PULVERIZE HIM
OR NOTHING.
HE JUST SORT OF DISAPPEARED,
EVAPORATED.
- TENSEIGA PROTECTED SESSHOMARU
AGAINST THE POWER AND LIGHT
OF TETSUSAIGA.
IT ACTED ON ITS OWN ACCORD.
- IT HAS A WILL OF IT OWN?
AND HERE, SESSHOMARU CALLED
THE TENSEIGA A USELESS SWORD,
AND HE DESPISED IT
AS HIS BIRTHRIGHT.
- TENSEIGA IS THE SWORD OF LIFE,
AND WHEN SESSHOMARU'S LIFE
WAS ENDANGERED,
DESPITE HIS DARK SOUL,
THE TENSEIGA CHOSE TO SAVE HIM,
AND THAT IS WHAT MAKES HIM
INVINCIBLE.
- SO HOW DO YOU DEFEAT
A FOOL LIKE THAT?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
IT'S BEYOND ME.
- HMM.
- I'VE SHARPENED THE SWORD
TO PERFECTION.
NOW YOU JUST HAVE
TO TRAIN YOURSELF TO DEFEAT
SESSHOMARU'S TENSEIGA
LIKE HE WAS TRYING TO DEFEAT
THE TETSUSAIGA.
SO BEFORE HE DIED,
THE GREAT DOG DEMON GAVE
EACH OF HIS SONS A SWORD.
HE GAVE THE TETSUSAIGA
TO INUYASHA
AND THE TENSEIGA TO SESSHOMARU.
THAT CUNNING OLD HOUND MUST HAVE
MADE IT SO THAT IT IS FUTILE
FOR THE BROTHERS TO FIGHT
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
I GUESS THEY'LL
LEARN THAT EVENTUALLY.
[RUSTLING]
- [GROWLS]
- [GASP]
HMM?
[GULP]
HMM.
- MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS, GIRL.
YOUR GENEROSITY IS WASTED.
I DON'T EAT HUMAN FOOD.
- [GASP]
UH...UM...
AH.
- I KNEW IT!
I KNEW YOU WERE
THE DIRTY CULPRIT, RIN.
- UH! UH! UH!
YOU'RE A LUCKY ORPHAN
TO HAVE THE VILLAGE TAKE YOU IN,
BUT YOU MUST NOT STEAL FISH
FROM THE PRESERVE.
- NEVER DO IT AGAIN.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
- DAMN, THAT'S A FREAKISH CHILD.
SHE NEVER SHOWS ANY SIGN
OF REMORSE OR FEAR.
- DISASTER HAS LEFT HER MUTE.
HER ENTIRE FAMILY
WAS SLAUGHTERED BY THIEVES,
AND SHE HASN'T SPOKEN SINCE,
SO CAN YOU BLAME HER?
[RUSTLING]
- NO, THANKS.
- UM.
UH.
- I TOLD YOU, I DON'T NEED
ANYTHING FROM YOU.
- UM.
[SIGH]
- WHERE DID YOU GET
THOSE BRUISES?
- UH...HUH?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
- UH.
HA HA! HA HA!
- WHAT ARE YOU SMILING ABOUT?
I SIMPLY ASKED A QUESTION.
I DON'T CARE. I'M JUST CURIOUS.
- HUH. UH. HA! UH.
HUH. UH. UH. UH. AHH.
- [SLURPING]
YEAH. AHH. OH, YEAH.
HUH?
WHAT, GIRL?
DOES THIS OLD HUT BELONG TO YOU?
- UH, MM.
- AAH! LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
HURRY! HURRY!
- DAMN IT!
THEY'VE CAUGHT UP ALREADY.
[MEN SHOUTING]
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
- HEH HEH HEH.
I HAD TO SEARCH
HIGH AND LOW FOR YOU,
YOU DIRTY THIEF.
NOW HAND OVER
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
THAT YOU STOLE FROM ME.
- ALL RIGHT.
I WON'T RUN AWAY.
YOU'RE LETTING ME GO?
THANK YOU FOR YOUR MERCY.
- HMM.
- AAAAGH!
- YOU FOOL.
I WOULD'VE FORGOTTEN.
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE GOTTEN WHAT I WANTED.
I'M GOING ON AHEAD.
YOU STAY IN THE VILLAGE
AND FEED TO YOUR HEARTS' DESIRE.
THEN CATCH UP WITH ME
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
- [GASP]
UH...UH...UH...
[ALL SCREAMING]
- IS SOMETHING
THE MATTER, KAGOME?
YOU SEEM VERY QUIET TODAY.
- IT'S VERY SLIGHT, BUT I'M SURE
I SENSE A JEWEL SHARD NEARBY.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS, KAGOME?
WHICH DIRECTION? CAN YOU TELL?
- [PANTING]
UH! OH!
UH...UH...AAH!
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
WHERE ARE YOU?
PLEASE ANSWER. PLEASE ANSWER ME.
IS IT POSSIBLE
THAT LORD SESSHOMARU
WAS CUT DOWN BY INUYASHA
WHEN HE WENT TO BATTLE WITH HIM?
CUT DOWN.
SPEAKING OF BEING
CUT DOWN--HMPH--
WHY SHOULD I CARE IF SESSHOMARU
WAS CUT DOWN OR NOT?
HE USED ME AS A GUINEA PIG
IN HIS SWORD EXPERIMENT
AND HIT ME WITH THE TENSEIGA
TO SEE IF IT WOULD
CUT ME THROUGH OR NOT.
HE SAID HE WAS
TESTING HIS SWORD,
BUT I'M SURE
HE WAS JUST TEASING ME.
HE WOULDN'T HAVE STRUCK ME
IF THERE WAS ANY DOUBT
THAT I WOULD BE REVIVED.
HE WAS TESTING.
HE WAS TEASING.
HE WAS TESTING. HE WAS TEASING.
HE WAS TESTING.
HE WAS TEASING.
HE WAS TESTING. HE WAS TESTING?
LORD SESSHOMARU!
WOULD YOU HAVE ACTUALLY RISKED
MY LIFE TO TEST YOUR SWORD?
YOU UNGRATEFUL DOG!
AAH!
[GASP]
LORD SESSHOMARU!
BEFORE I CONTINUE
IN YOUR SERVICE,
WERE YOU ACTUALLY
TESTING YOUR SWORD ON ME?
- I EXPECTED A RELIEVED WELCOME
FROM YOU, JAKEN,
NOT AN INTERROGATION.
- HA HA HA! RIGHT.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE WELL.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT BE DEAD.
OOH!
- HMM. BLOOD.
BLOOD AND THE SMELL OF WOLVES.
I RECOGNIZE THIS BLOOD.
- WHAT IS THAT?
PHEW, PHEW. OH, SHE'S A GONER.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
SHE MUST'VE BEEN
ATTACKED BY WOLVES.
LOOK AT THE TEETH MARKINGS.
DO YOU RECOGNIZE
THIS PATHETIC HUMAN?
- HA HA! HA HA!
- WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, SIRE?
- INTERESTING.
I CAN SEE THEM.
THEY ARE FROM THE UNDERWORLD.
I'LL DO ANOTHER TEST.
I'LL USE THE TENSEIGA.
- [GASP] ANOTHER TEST?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, SIRE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YAAAAGH!
- DUH...OH, OH. HUH?
- MM...MM...HUH?
- SHE CAME BACK TO LIFE.
LORD SESSHOMARU,
YOU RESURRECTED THAT HUMAN GIRL
WITH THE POWER OF THE TENSEIGA?
HUH?
HELLO? LORD SESSHOMARU?
LORD SESSHOMARU
SAVING A HUMAN GIRL
IS SURPRISING ENOUGH,
BUT THEN AGAIN,
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
DIDN'T LORD SESSHOMARU JUST SAY
HE WAS GOING TO TEST THE POWER
OF THE TENSEIGA ONCE AGAIN?
TH-THAT WOULD MEAN
I WAS CUT DOWN WITH NO
GUARANTEE FOR SURVIVAL.
AND TO THINK I'VE DEVOTED MYSELF
TO YOU ALL OF THESE YEARS.
[SOBBING]
LORD SESSHOMARU, IT'S SO UNFAIR!
WHY DO YOU DO IT?
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND IT.
[SOBS]
UH? HUH? WHAT?
LORD SESSHOMARU, WAIT!
I'M COMING!
- HUH. TENSEIGA...
YOU COMPELLED ME
TO SAVE A HUMAN LIFE TODAY.
- OH.
- A MASSACRE.
- HEY! IS ANYONE HERE
LEFT ALIVE?
- WAS THIS DONE
BY A PACK OF WOLVES?
- THEY LEFT
THEIR TRACKS EVERYWHERE.
- THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
A GREAT DEAL OF THEM.
THINK THEY WERE POSSESSED
BY THE JEWEL SHARD
THAT KAGOME SENSED?
- HMM. PROBABLY.
THIS SLAUGHTER HAS DEMON
WRITTEN ALL OVER IT.
- [GROWING]
- AAH! LOOK OUT!
THE WOLVES ARE SURROUNDING US!
- HUH! LET'S TEACH
THESE WOLVES A LESSON.
THEY'RE STRAY.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEIR LEADER
ISN'T EVEN HERE.
THEY'RE USELESS IN BATTLE
UNLESS THEY'RE IN A PACK.
UH! YAH!
YAAAH!
- [HOWLING]
- UH! THEY'RE HOWLING.
- THEY'RE CALLING
FOR THEIR COMRADES.
- [GASP]
I CAN SENSE THE POWER
OF A SACRED JEWEL SHARD,
AND IT'S COMING AT US
REALLY FAST.
- UH?
- UH.
- UGH.
- HUH?
- THAT GUY JUST FLEW
RIGHT OUT OF THE TORNADO.
- JUST WHO ARE YOU?
EXPLAIN YOURSELVES.
WHY ARE YOU KILLING MY WOLVES?
- UH, 3 SHARDS.
HE HAS ONE ON HIS RIGHT ARM
AND ONE ON EACH OF HIS LEGS.
- HEH. SO YOU'RE
THE ONE CONTROLLING
THIS BLOODTHIRSTY PACK.
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- A PACK OF POSSESSED WOLVES
WIPED OUT AN ENTIRE VILLAGE.
THEY'RE CONTROLLED BY A MAN
WITH 3 JEWEL SHARDS.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE DEMONS
ARE BATTLING FOR TERRITORY
IN THIS NECK OF THE WOODS.
A DARK SHADOW
CUTS THROUGH THE WIND.
I CAN FEEL IT.
IS IT ANOTHER
SACRED JEWEL SHARD?
DO I SENSE THE ONES
ON HIS ARMS AND LEGS?
NO. I FEEL IT COMING
FROM THE SKY.
NEXT ON "INUYASHA"...
SEE YOU SOON.