[SERVANT A] She's right
through this door, sir.
Why thank you.
Uh?!
[OBI]
I, uh... Hello, Miss?
Obi!
Wow, dancing instead of
herbs. That's a shock.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, good! All right, come on.
I really need you
to practice with me!
You what?
[TEACHER A]
No, no, it's fine!
Shirayuki is, uh...
she seems to finally be
getting the hang of it.
Is that the dance teacher?
Yes, and I keep stepping
on his poor toes.
I feel bad for him.
So you wanna step on me?
Yes, if you don't mind!
Well, I'd love to, but
I can't at the moment.
I'm on my way to guard Mihaya,
otherwise, I, y'know, would.
Oh, right.
I was also wanting to
go down to the port
to see if I could find anything
else out, but that's okay.
You and the master.
You're both always
so dependable.
But don't you have
your hands kinda full
with all that getting ready
to go to Tanbarun stuff?
From dancing lessons for
the ball to table etiquette
and appropriate
court... whatever.
You have a lot to do, don't you?
Leave it to me and the prince.
We can handle investigating
the pretty boy.
Here you go.
The Chief Herbalist asked
me to give this to you,
and Ryu wanted you
to have these herbs
that will help with sore feet.
Thank you.
[OBI]
Well, get to it.
[door closes]
[sighs] Obi. Has he left, yet?
He has. He doesn't
enjoy being the guard
for that mountain
monkey, though.
Well, at least not every day.
We should hopefully find
out something soon.
[ZEN]
Indeed.
A mysterious kid
named Kazuki, huh?
[SOLDIER A] A pretty boy
with his hair tied up?
[OBI]
His name is Kazuki,
and we had high hopes
for him in our troupe,
but he claimed all he'd ever
wanted to be was a knight.
Then, one day, he just
up and ran away
with all the troupe's money.
[SOLDIER A] Brat sounds
like quite a handful.
If a kid like that
shows up, y'know,
sayin' he wants to join the
knights or work at the castle,
do you guys think you could
hang on to him for me?
[SOLDIER A]
Sure. We can keep an eye out.
[OBI] All right, might as well
go through all the boats.
When you're talking to soldiers,
wouldn't it be easier
just to tell them
you work for the prince?
[OBI] Maybe, but I'm not used
to working like that.
[MIHAYA] Hm? What do you mean
you're not used to it?
That's your job, right?
Aren't you Prince
Zen's attendant?
Who knows.
[MIHAYA]
Who knows?!
Why don't you focus on
keeping an eye out, yeah?
You are the only one who knows
what this Kazuki boy looks like.
It's because no one believes
you work at the castle, right?
The way you speak and dress
isn't exactly court appropriate.
Not to mention I'm
with a mountain monkey
who wears a lady's scarf.
A lady's scarf? Hey, shut
up, you've got one, too!
And a stray-cat face!
Just to be clear, you and I
are not equals, got it?!
I have noble blood in my veins!
You're a peasant and
can't accomplish anything,
but I, on the other--
[OBI] It doesn't matter
what my position is
or what you can or
can't accomplish.
If you even try to meddle
with Shirayuki or my master,
I'll tie you up
with that neck scarf
and send you back
to the mountains.
[OBI]
Move it!
[SHIRAYUKI sighs]
[SHIRAYUKI] I can only do
what I can do right now.
[SHIRAYUKI] And that's
what I should be doing.
How'd I get here?
[gasps]
Shirayuki?
Shirayuki!
[ZEN grunting]
Is that Obi's?
When did he come by?
[ZEN exhales]
We don't have a
single lead. Still.
She's leaving tomorrow,
and nothing.
What else can I do?
[footsteps]
[OBI]
Miss Kiki! Mitsuhide!
[grunts]
I wonder where you two
might be headed together
at this time of night.
Huh?!
What's he mean. "Huh?" Huh?
We're going to get Zen.
He hasn't come back yet.
Back from where?
[ZEN grunting]
[MITSUHIDE] Zen, it's time
to come back, now!
[ZEN]
All right.
Training alone?
Is that normal for him?
Only since he found
out about those guys
looking for Shirayuki.
After she was ordered
to go to Tanbarun,
he started training at night.
[ZEN grunting]
[OBI] You'd think he doesn't
actually wanna let her leave,
wouldn't you?
Possibly.
But it's more likely he
just wants to protect her.
[KIKI, MITSUHIDE]
Uh?!
Obi. Didn't see you there.
[OBI] I think the two of us
should have a match.
Huh?
Master, if I win
please let me be
Shirayuki's attendant.
I'll protect her for you.
I'm assuming you
can't go with her.
Allow me to take your
place by her side.
You trusted me to be her guard,
so it would only be
an extension of my job.
[ZEN exhales]
[BOTH grunting]
Wow. You really are light
on your feet, Obi!
[BOTH grunting]
[OBI gasps]
[ZEN yells]
[OBI gasping]
Consider this match over.
[OBI]
Mm?
Congrats. You won,
fair and square.
[OBI]
Uh...
Fighting with swords
is one thing,
but I'm fairly certain I
couldn't beat you unarmed.
[OBI]
Are you sure about this?
[ZEN] I told my brother I
would send someone I trust.
Allowing you to be that someone
wouldn't be much of a
surprise to anybody.
But if Shirayuki
complains about it,
I'll deny any responsibility.
Come on, you could help me out
just a little there, Master!
[ZEN] I suppose I can go tell
her about it, but that's all.
[knocking]
[ZEN]
Shirayuki?
[gasps]
Shh!
Sorry to bother you.
Can we talk for a bit?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, um... Sure.
Come on in.
[ZEN]
No, not here.
This is your room, so it would
be considered inappropriate.
[gasping]
I know a place not far
away where we can talk.
Let's go there if possible.
Right, that sounds fine.
[ZEN]
Since you're leaving tomorrow,
I thought you'd be
busy getting ready,
but it looked like you
were sleeping instead.
No, I wasn't. I was
reading a book on herbs.
The chief herbalist
gave it to me earlier.
I was hoping it would help
me sleep a little better.
[ZEN]
A book on herbs?
Yep, I'll sleep like a log.
I had a match with Obi,
and decided he should
be your attendant.
What?!
He'll go with you to Tanbarun.
His entire job is
to look after you.
Obi?
Now, about what people
will think in Tanbarun,
as well as the guys
who are looking for you.
The truth is, there are a lot
of things I want to tell you,
but for some reason,
I can't manage to do it.
I wish I could explain why.
Don't worry about that.
I wish I could explain
how talking to you
makes me feel better,
but I can't.
Besides,
I was able to get through
the last lesson today
without stepping on the
dance teacher's feet
or even tripping over
the hem of my dress.
At the very least,
I think I should be ready
for Tanbarun's ball.
[ZEN]
Now that you mention it,
is that scrape on your
arm a dance injury?
Uh. Yeah, it's my war wound.
I skinned my knees, too.
It wasn't pretty.
[ZEN]
Heh. Dancing is dangerous.
Well, good night,
and sweet dreams.
[ZEN]
Yeah.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI gasping]
I hope you have a good night.
I will.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[BOTH laugh]
[SHILA, KAI]
Good work.
[KAI]
Uh. Hey, look.
There's a carriage down there
by the Starlight Gate.
No way! It's Shirayuki!
What? Seriously?
I can't imagine with
Shirayuki's rank
they'd actually open the gate
for her if she's alone.
[KAI] Do you think she's
going out with the prince?
[OBI sighs]
Nobody cares that
I'd rather travel light.
They made me bring about a
thousand changes of clothes.
[SHIRAYUKI] Will you be
in the carriage with me?
[OBI] Nope. I'll follow
behind you on horseback.
Well, okay, then.
I didn't even know you were the
one going with me to Tanbarun
as my attendant until
late last night.
Oh, what a surprise. I'm really
looking forward to it.
You know, I am too.
Thanks for coming
along with me, Obi.
So, uh...
I have a question for you.
Yes?
Did anyone mention how I ended
up becoming your attendant?
What do you mean?
[OBI] Hmph. If the master
didn't say, then it's a secret.
[SHIRAYUKI] No fair! You're
the one who brought it up!
[OBI laughs]
I guess I can at least tell you
that the master was the one
who wanted to go back with
you to Tanbarun the most.
I'd like it if we could,
at the very minimun,
find Kazuki while Shirayuki
is away from the castle.
As do I.
[ZEN] Counting travel time and
the days she'll be in Tabarun,
she'll be gone for a month.
Would you like me
to arrange a way
to go meet her somewhere
along the route back?
Yes, but I expect there will
be some quarreling first.
[KIKI]
Mm?
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh?
[HARUKA] You look as if you have
something controversial to say
about my accompanying
you on this journey.
No. Sir, I don't think
anything of the sort!
[OBI] Miss. Are you all
right over he-- [whimpering]
[HARUKA]
Hm? Uh! Obi?
[OBI gasps]
Lord Haruka, please forgive
me, that was terribly rude.
Word has it that
you've been chosen
to be Prince Zen's
messenger, now.
Uh... You knew about that?
[HARUKA]
I heard from the prince
that one of his attendants would
be going to Tanbarun, as well,
but I didn't think it'd be you.
[OBI]
I didn't either, sir.
[ZEN] Oh, you're all here!
I came to see you off.
Greeting, Highness.
Might I have a moment
of your time?
[ZEN]
Of course, Lord Haruka.
Apparently, the duke
will go along with us
until we get near the border.
What?!
[SERVANT B] Prince Zen, the
carriage is ready for travel.
[GUARD A]
By your leave, highness.
I entrust this journey to
your hands, Lord Haruka.
Highness.
Don't let us down, Obi.
I won't.
Excuse me, Prince Zen.
Do you have... like
an object with you,
something that I can borrow
while I'm in Tanbarun?
Something to borrow?
That's right, like a pin,
or a button maybe.
[ZEN]
Will a pocket watch work?
Uh! Yes.
I will give it back
to you when I return.
[gasps]
Thank you.
Uh?
[ZEN]
Lord Brother!
Don't worry about me.
Just watching everyone leave.
I'll be back, Prince Zen.
Bye, Kiki.
Bye, Mitsuhide.
See you in about a month.
[ZEN]
Lord Brother!
I didn't think you'd
bother to show up.
I wanted to see you depressed,
but you didn't look all
that miserable to me.
Although, it was
still rewarding.
What's that supposed to mean?
Zen.
What?
Shall I tell you one
thing I learned from her,
that pretty little redheaded
peasant of yours?
What are you talking about?
Uh?
It's in the eyes.
Eyes are windows to the soul.
I hope they aren't clouded
when she returns.
[KIKI] She's supposed to be
in Tanbarun for seven days.
I hope she'll choose to
come back afterwards.
[MITSUHIDE]
As do I.
But if things seem off at all,
it's not like we have
to just wait around.
Besides, you know Zen. He's
scary when he gets angry.
Very true.
[MITSUHIDE] I have this feeling
I should've talked to Obi first.
Asked him what he thought
of Zen and Shirayuki.
[OBI] I'm assuming you
can't go with her?
Allow me to take your
place by her side.
[MITSUHIDE]
Is that too boorish?
Even if I asked him,
it's hard to know if
he'd tell me the truth.
Clarines and Tanbarun
are allies,
and they have benefited
from each other's growth
and development.
Together, they've been acquiring
land, technology, and education.
However, we do not interfere
with the goings-on in
the other's castle.
Observe Tanbarun's court first.
Only then will you
be able to determine
the appropriate action.
Yes, my lord.
[SHIRAYUKI]
How can I know what I should do
when I don't know what I can do?
[bell tolls]
Hey, Shirayuki,
can you grab me a bundle
of tartsugi herb, please?
[GARAK] Preparing medicine
for a new prescription?
Yes.
I think she should be
arriving at Tanbarun around now.
Right.
[SHIRAYUKI] Lord Haruka,
thank you very much.
Please be careful
on your way back.
Try to keep this in mind, girl.
You were invited to
attend Tanbarun's ball
and ordered by
Prince Izana to go.
Don't come back in disgrace.
The same to you!
Sir!
Cranky old man.
So, you ready to
finish this journey?
[SHIRAYUKI]
I think so!
The question is,
is Tanbarun ready?
[OBI] Good, it looks like we
haven't been followed so far.
[gasps] Miss Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm?
[gasps] I, uh...
Do ya... wanna ride my horse?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh. To the castle...?
[OBI]
Right! Never mind.
[OBI] She must be glad to
see her homeland again.
I hope it doesn't
disappoint her.
[RAJ] I appreciate you
traveling all this way.
It's very nice to see
you again, Shirayuki.
How was your journey?
It was fine, Your Highness.
Thank you so much for
the gracious invitation.
I'm honored.
[RAJ]
Well, then. Right this way.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Something's different.
Maybe what I've heard is right,
and he really has turned
over a new leaf.
[RAJ sighs]
[RAJ]
Well, now, answer me something.
Of course.
Why on earth did you come here?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
She came here, Prince Raj,
because you invited her.
Yes, I know that, but
I wasn't asking you!
I came here, Prince Raj,
because you invited me to come.
Yeah, I know.
I asked you to the ball
as a gesture of thanks.
After our conversation
in Clarines,
I felt like I was in your
debt for some reason.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[RAJ]
I can't tell you why, though.
I'm sure you've noticed.
Prince Raj tends to be
"wishy-washy," as they say
What do you mean
I'm wishy-washy?!
[SAKAKI]
I suggested he invite you
as a way of showing his
appreciation for your advice
as well as his
newfound humanity.
[RAJ]
What?!
I was already planning
to invite her! [growls]
Oh. By the way,
who's the guy with you?
I don't believe we've met.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, yes, I'm sorry.
He accompanied me
here from Clarines.
It's a pleasure to make your
acquaintance, Highness.
I'm Shirayuki's guard.
My name's Obi.
I've been entrusted
to secure her safety
while she's in Tanbarun.
I was sent under Prince
Zen's direct orders.
[RAJ] Shirayuki, I have
another question for you.
Did Prince Zen have an opinion
regarding this invitation?
[SHIRAYUKI]
No, not that I know of.
[RAJ]
Oh! I see.
I have an idea, Prince Raj.
Why don't you stay with
Shirayuki as much as possible
while she's here with us?
[RAJ]
Uh!
Sakaki, why would you
say something like that?
[SAKAKI] I don't understand
why you're so surprised.
You're the one who
invited her to come,
so you must to make
her feel welcome.
[RAJ grunts]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Hm?
Why aren't you saying
very much, Shirayuki?
I mean, there has to be
something in this for you,
doesn't there?
[SHIRAYUKI]
I do not know.
I've never spent a
long period of time
with you before now,
Your Highness.
I do feel this is
a great opportunity
for everyone, though.
Uh? Is that so?
Yes, I do think it's so.
We might as well try, right?
[RAJ gasps]
[RAJ] If you insist, Shirayuki,
I suppose it cannot be helped.
[RAJ] Allow me to welcome
you back to Tanbarun.
[RONA] So someone managed
to change our big brother.
[IZANA]
What is it?
[RONA] What if all those
rumors are true and she
really is special?! Shirayuki.
[IZANA] Oh, come now.
Why do you look so surprised?
[RONA] Tell the truth!
Are you in love with her?!
[RAJ]
Uh...!