Shirayuki!
Found you!
Let go of me!
[OBI groans]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi!
[KAZUKI] I'm taking you to
where you truly belong.
Pops is gonna be so happy.
Good. So you're awake.
[KAZUKI]
What the...?!
Umihebi?!
[rustling]
[KAZUKI] After we took
you out of the castle,
you and I were attacked by
one of those evil woman's
companions when we
were by ourselves.
So in other words,
you're saying
I was kidnapped
from my kidnappers?
I'm so sorry,
but you won't be able
to go back home anymore.
[SHIRAYUKI whimpers]
[ZEN]
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
Do you maybe wanna
sneak into town?
What?
Like right now?
Well, that sounds fun, too.
But you are leaving
for Tanbarun tomorrow.
I think we might get in
trouble if we went tonight.
That's true.
We'll go when you get
back from your trip.
Just us.
[SHIRAYUKI] That moment
feels like a lifetime ago.
I haven't heard Zen's voice in
what seems like an eternity.
[SHIRAYUKI whimpers]
[KAZUKI]
Now's our chance.
We have to get out
before things get worse.
Shirayuki. Can you do this?
I know it's scary.
I can!
Whoa, what are you doing?!
[SHIRAYUKI] Would you want to
wear this during an escape?
[KAZUKI]
Uh.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I have to be strong.
[SHIRAYUKI] Kazuki, let me
have a look at your face.
[gasps] Why?
It's nothing.
We need to treat it before the
swelling gets any worse, okay?
[KAZUKI]
I, uh...
Nah, We'll do it later.
[KAZUKI] Damn it!
We're already on the boat.
I was afraid of that.
Now what?
There's not a lot of movement,
so the ship must be anchored.
With any luck, we're
still close to the shore.
[KAZUKI grunting]
She locked it,
so we're not going to be
able to sneak up on deck.
Knowing her, there're
probably guards, anyway.
Got any ideas?
[gasps]
It's a Chitoka seed!
[SHIRAYUKI]
I think I've got a plan.
Why do we get stuck
guarding these two brats
when we could be ashore,
having some fun?
[yawns]
[PIRATE B]
Quit complaining.
If you want to go, go.
You'll get beat senseless,
but who cares.
Uh?! Hey, look!
[PIRATE A gasping]
Come on!
[PIRATE A yelps]
[PIRATES coughing]
[PIRATE B]
Did those kids set a fire?!
[PIRATE A]
I can't see anything!
Kazuki!
[PIRATE A]
Hey!
[BOTH groan]
[KAZUKI]
I can't believe it,
your plan worked!
What are those things?
[SHIRAYUKI] Chitoka seeds.
They're a good food source,
and they also happen to smoke
a lot when you burn them.
I figured we could use
that to our advantage.
Just out of curiosity, what
did you do back in Clarines?
I'm an apprentice to the
chief court herbalist.
Fascinating.
Is that what you wanted
to do with your life?
Yes, absolutely.
[KAZUKI]
All right.
It looks like the coast
is clear out there.
Now, when you get up on deck,
break left and run.
Then, jump off into the water.
[KAZUKI gasping]
[UMIHEBI] Where are you dears
off to in such a hurry?!
You look like little minnows.
Careful, this snake'll
swallow you head first.
Hey!
We're almost there.
[MITSUHIDE]
Prince Zen, look!
We found this.
[gasps] My watch.
[MITSUHIDE] Apparently, Obi
picked it up at after the fight.
When he went in search of
Shirayuki he left it here.
[SHIRAYUKI] I will give it
back to you when I return.
[ZEN]
I see.
Huh?
[MIHAYA]
Uh!
[ZEN]
Ah! What... was that for?
It's not that we
don't appreciate you
maintaining your composure
throughout all this.
But you need to vent some of
your frustration and anger.
If not, you'll
spontaneously combust.
Heh.
So you're just helping me
burn off some of the steam?
That's oh, so kind of you.
[MITSUHIDE]
Was it too hard?
[ZEN]
I'll put it this way,
you're going straight to
the Punishment Chamber
when we get back Mitsuhide.
Ah! Why just me?
It was Kiki's idea!
Wise decision, Prince Zen.
There is one more thing, though.
Obi left this message for you.
[gasps]
[RAJ] Thank you for waiting.
Ready to go?
The plan is to visit a
self-governing vigilante group.
Although, they prefer
to be called
the Lions of the Mountain,
they're mostly known
for fighting bandits,
but they've taken on the
Claw of the Sea before.
Interesting. Hopefully they'll
have useful information.
Also, you'll be happy
to hear this.
[RAJ]
What?
I have a promising lead.
[whistle blows]
[MUKAZE] According to Itoya's
account of the ordeal,
the Claw left their mark at
the scene of the disappearance.
They most likely
tracked down Kazuki
and took him back to the ship,
along with the girl.
Contact our men in the village!
And prepare the ship.
We're going after the Claw!
[MEN]
Yeah!
[MAN A]
Let's move out!
What about you?
There's something that
I want to look into.
I'll need your help.
[MUKAZE]
You, over there!
[OBI grunts]
[MUKAZE] Itoya informed me
who you've been working for.
Do you intend to tell the
prince about our operations?
All you need to know is I'm not
gonna let you out of my sight.
[PIRATE A groans]
[PIRATE B yelps]
[PIRATES groaning]
[coughs]
I see you're still as cruel
as you've always been!
Those men are your comrades.
Sometimes bad boys
need to be hurt a little.
That way they'll
learn their lesson.
I think they both have
severe internal bleeding.
The one farthest from
us is hyperventilating,
which is a bad sign.
[UMIHEBI]
Oh!
So you know a thing or two
about medicine, my pet.
Don't touch her!
Oh, are you a hero, now?
[KAZUKI growls]
[yelps]
Failing at a job is one thing,
but you of all
people should know
what happens to those
who disrespect me.
Dolls are meant to be
beautiful and silent.
Otherwise, no one'll
want to play with them.
I'm not a doll for anyone.
I'm a Lion of the
Mountain, now and forever!
Please don't tell me
you think those idiots
are on their way to save you.
[KAZUKI] Pops isn't a cruel,
heartless delinquent!
He's nothing like you!
So you do think he's coming.
Sounds like your pretty face
has made you delusional.
[KAZUKI]
It's not just me!
[UMIHEBI] Hm? You mean this
darling redheaded thing
is important to the
Lions of the Mountain?
Oh, do tell.
[KAZUKI growls]
[UMIHEBI] And don't leave out
a single detail, either.
They're about two
kilometers ahead of us,
to the south-southeast.
All right. Move quickly!
[bird squawks]
[OBI]
Huh?
Why'd you stop?
[ITOYA]
Who is that?!
There you are...
Obi.
I failed you, master. I'm sorry.
Ha, ha! I'm sorry, too! That hit
was from Kiki and Mitsuhide.
What is with that weird voice
you're using, anyway?
You'll scare people if
you don't knock that off.
[OBI]
You mean Shirayuki?
No, fool. I mean Ryu.
[OBI]
Hm. Guess you're right.
"I'm leaving and
taking the package
for Shirayuki from Prince Zen."
You could've given more
details, but it was helpful.
And it worked.
Good.
[OBI]
I wasn't sure if you'd learned
how to train the birds,
yet. I'm impressed.
I had Kihal show me
the ropes, first.
Then I snuck in and blended
with the soldiers.
Whoa, that's unbelievable.
He taught that bird to
follow the sound of a bell?
[chirps]
I wish Shirayuki was
here to see it, though.
Who might the two of you be?
[SAKAKI]
I know one of them is the leader
of the Lions of the Mountain.
[MUKAZE] Oh, so someone here
thinks they know my face.
The Lions of the Mountain.
[MIHAYA]
Your Highness,
I know where I've seen the man
with the ponytail and scar.
He was the one in the port
with the boy that night.
[ZEN] These are the men
who kidnapped Shirayuki?
Wait, what are you
talking about?!
I thought we already established
that the Claw of the
Sea took Shirayuki.
Kazuki took her from the
castle along with Itoya,
the guy with the
ponytail over there,
and, they are Lions
of the Mountain.
But then, when
Itoya stepped away,
she was taken again,
with Kazuki.
That time it was probably
the Claw of the Sea.
[RAJ]
What?! I don't understand this!
Lion of the Mountain fellows,
explain it to me!
Are you people
from the government?
We are.
I am Prince Raj Schenezade
of Tanbarun!
[ITOYA, MUKAZE grunt]
[RAJ] I demand that you give me
all the information you have!
What do you know
about the girl?!
I honestly couldn't care
less what you demand.
[gasps]
[MUKAZE]
Shall we go?
[ZEN] I'm curious as to your
reason for refusing him.
My understanding was this:
The Lions formed
to fight bandits
and protect the citizens.
So I'm confused why you were the
ones who snuck into the castle.
Why would you use
violence against Obi?
Why take an innocent girl?
For the kid.
Kazuki was a slave to the
Claw before he joined with us.
Itoya!
[ITOYA]
After they'd had enough of him,
they sold him to some nobles
who only kept him around
because he was pretty.
They treated him
like a living doll.
That's why!
When Kazuki heard Shirayuki's
story, he identified
with an unfortunate girl
who was stolen by a prince
against her will just because
her red hair caught his eye!
He wanted to take her to a place
where such fools
couldn't find her.
[ZEN]
And how did that work out?
What did Shirayuki say
when you told her?
Did she agree to go with you?
You didn't let her have a
say in the matter, did you?
You dragged her out by force.
[gasps]
We were a bit too rough
with her. I'm sorry for that.
I can tell you're close
with Shirayuki.
That you care.
Yes. I will save her.
[MUKAZE]
The Lions of the Mountain
are people that have grown
tired of noble tyranny.
They've been driven from
their homes unjustly.
They're who we are
and who we protect.
We don't abide by
the rule of kings.
That's why our people trust us.
But we want to save those
kids as much as you do.
So, since we share
a common goal,
we might as well work together.
Will you agree to let the
rest go and move forward?
Well, Raj? Agreed?
Uh! Oh, yeah, I guess. Sure.
Then it's a deal.
[ZEN] An entire port town
working for the Claw?
Yes.
We've had our eye on that
place for quite some time.
There's a wharf there,
which is convenient.
I'd say it's definitely
worth checking out.
[ZEN]
I see.
What's the matter, Mihaya?
I've never seen you so serious.
Oh, you know, just feeling
like more of an outsider
now than I ever have
before, that's all.
Even that stray cat
bastard is in the fold.
But it's fine.
I'll let you know if I have
anything that needs to be said.
Oh, I can't wait!
I don't believe I was
addressing you, you--
Stray cat bastard?
We'll be at the port town
once we clear this next hill.
Hey, was that your real voice?
I think you forgot to use
the scary one this time.
[OBI]
Huh?
[MUKAZE] That's definitely
one of the Claw's boats.
See that ship anchored
at the wharf?
Yeah. I wonder if their
boss lady's on that one.
For the first time ever, I
actually hope that she is.
You mean the Claw of the
Sea's leader is a woman?
[MUKAZE] Yes, but she's more
like a snake than anything.
Cold, dead eyes with
a heart to match.
She terrifies weak men into
doing whatever she says.
No matter how miserable it might
make them in the long run.
Obi. What'd you find?
Seems we hit the jackpot.
Some guys said they saw
a pretty, blonde boy
around earlier.
He was being escorted
onto the Claw ship
that's anchored at the wharf.
Kazuki.
[ZEN]
And Shirayuki?
I couldn't find anyone
who had seen her.
Although, just because
they didn't see her
doesn't mean she isn't there.
[ITOYA] In a way, this is
like a hostage situation.
They have the upper hand
if we try to pick a fight.
Which makes things difficult.
So then, how do we proceed?
Wait until the crew
goes into town
and sneak them off the ship?
[KIKI]
Prince Zen.
I have a proposal that
I think could work.
[PIRATE C]
Huh?
28, 29, 30!
You're going to kill him!
Please, stop! You don't
have to do this!
Fine, pull him up.
Yes, ma'am.
[KAZUKI coughs, pants]
[UMIHEBI]
Are you just dyin' to talk now?
Come on, why do
those silly Lions
want that precious Red so badly?
I told you. I don't
know anything.
They never let me in on it.
All I overheard is that
it was some kind of job
they were doing.
Then, we still haven't convinced
you to stop playing dumb?
I suppose it doesn't matter.
Oh, girlie, why don't we
figure out which master
I get to sell you off to?
You stand out so much.
I think I should send you so
far away from your homeland
that no one will
ever recognize you.
You can't make me go.
I'm not scared of you.
[PIRATE C]
Boss, you've got a visitor!
They wanna make a deal!
Tell 'em she's busy!
[PIRATE C] Uh, looks like
pretty high quality goods!
[UMIHEBI growls]
They had better be.
Throw these brats
back in their room.
When I'm done with this,
we set sail.
[PIRATES]
Yes, ma'am!
[PIRATE C] I was looking
forward to more time ashore.
[PIRATE D] You can get just
as drunk at sea as on land.
[PIRATE C]
Yeah, that's true. Ha, ha!
Uh?
Try to relax. You need to
rest as much as you can.
Don't you want the truth?
About what's going on.
Who I actually am.
And why I was trying to find
you in the first place.
[SHIRAYUKI]
It doesn't matter.
You hurt my friend Obi
at the castle that night,
so it's not like I can trust
everything you'd tell me anyway.
However, just now, up on deck,
you endured a lot of pain,
and kept your mouth
shut for your friends.
I can at least
trust that action.
Uh?
Besides, we can talk about
it when this is over.
As soon as we get out
of here and we're safe.
Let's do that.
[BOTH gasp]
[PIRATE C]
Set sail!
Damn it! They've pulled
up the anchor.
We've started moving again!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen.
[PIRATES laughing]
[door creaking]
[PIRATE D] You stay in here
and keep quiet, or else!
[KAZUKI]
Uh?
What kind of girl gets
sold 'cause the jail
doesn't know what to do with
her, for cryin' out loud?
[KAZUKI]
Hey, wait!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Um, Miss, are you all right?
[gasps] Kiki!
[MITSUHIDE] You want to
pretend to be a criminal
and get sold to the Claw?
They're less likely to be
suspicious of a woman.
At the very least, if Shirayuki
is on the ship like we think,
then she'll have a
friend to protect her.
Bad idea, don't let her!
That'd be way too dangerous!
We have to save her somehow.
I'm willing to take this risk
if it gets us any closer.
Your Highness,
I have some information
that you might want.
What is it?
Their base would
be weak right now
with the boss and
her crew at sea.
[ZEN]
What do you mean?
[MIHAYA] You remember that
my father was a count,
and that he circulated
with all kinds of people?
[ZEN]
I do.
The pirates, a female leader,
the back room deals.
Memories are flooding back
of my crooked father
and ruined older brother.
I think they were in
business with the Claw.
[BOTH gasp]
[MIHAYA] In fact, my family
was in so deep with them
that we were
once invited back
to the main base
of their operation.
[ZEN]
Wait.
Are you saying you
remember how to find it?
[MUKAZE]
Impressive.
We've been searching for years,
but I don't think we've come
close to locating their mansion.
Now, I probably wouldn't
be offering to help
if the situation
wasn't so desperate,
but this information
will cost you.
[ZEN growls]
Why am I surprised?
Of course you'd say that.
Mihaya, will you
please tell us wh--
This actually doesn't concern
Prince Zen or Clarines.
The Claw of the Sea's base
is in Tanbarun territory.
That means it concerns
you, Prince Raj.
This is technically
your problem.
Are you willing to
give me what I want
in exchange for the information?
Very well.
[MIHAYA]
Seriously?!
You're certainly not
the first scoundrel
to sell information to Tanbarun.
And I want to save Shirayuki.
If, in the process,
you can help us root out
a festering scourge on our
kingdom, I'd be grateful.
Such a gift warrants
a handsome reward.
Right, Sakaki?
[SAKAKI]
Indeed.
Keep it safe.
I will.
[KIKI]
Your Highness.
Let's go over the plan.
It's you!
Yes, I'm here.
Uh! Wait, you know each other?
You must be Kazuki.
The chief has been
worried about you.
Pops said that?
Shirayuki. I'm so
relieved to see you.
We tricked them into throwing
me in here like this.
There's nothing to worry
about now, all right?
Zen's very close by.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Zen's here?
In Tanbarun?
Yes. He came to save you.
[SHIRAYUKI cries]
[KIKI]
You're going home.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thank you.
[RAJ]
Pirates!
Understand that we will not
allow you to get away from us!
[ZEN]
Let go of Shirayuki.
Believe me, I am not one
you want to trifle with!
[UMIHEBI]
Do you care to die?!
[RAJ]
Don't underestimate... Tanbarun.