[SHIRAYUKI]
All right. Now I'm done.
That's quite a haul
you've got there.
Working too hard as usual?
Hi, Obi!
Oh, wow! You're in uniform.
[OBI] They're having special
guests at the castle today,
so the master said I had to be.
But it feels weird. I'm not used
to wearing such fancy clothing.
I'm still tryin' to keep
up with all the rules
they have around here.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I feel the same way,
but I'm determined to
stay on this path.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ryu! Are you ready yet?
It's about time to
go back! Hey, Ryu!
[OBI] I don't think
he can hear you.
[bird chirps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh?
After all, the view
at my side is beautiful.
[SHIRAYUKI] And I know
there's even more scenery
down the road waiting for me.
[whistling]
[bird chirps]
[RYU gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
C'mon, Ryu! It's time to go!
[RYU]
Uh?
[whistling]
[SHIRAYUKI, OBI]
Uh?
Did she call that
bird with a whistle?
Sure looked like it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Um, thank you very much, miss.
You got Ryu's attention.
Look at your red hair.
I've never seen
anything like it before!
I know, I get that a lot.
Speaking of surprises,
that was amazing what you
just did with the bird!
You're the first person
I've actually talked to
since I arrived. I was a
ball of nerves until now.
What are you here for?
It's sort of a business meeting.
I have to speak with the Second
Prince about something big.
You're meeting Prince Zen?
Are you one of the guests
he said was visiting today?
[KIHAL]
I don't think so.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh?
[KIHAL]
This is great.
I could really use
someone to talk to.
Do you have an extra
minute by chance?
[SHIRAYUKI] Um, I still
haven't finished my shift.
[RYU] Don't worry,
we're not in any rush.
It's almost your break time,
anyway. I'll go back first.
Thanks!
[KIHAL]
So, what's your name?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Shirayuki.
I'm an apprentice court
herbalist here at the castle.
Nice to meet you,
I'm Kihal Toghrul.
But I'm not good at this formal
stuff, so call me Kihal.
Oh! And over there's
my good friend, Popo.
[SHIRAYUKI]
You're friends with it?
That's the most beautiful
bird I've ever laid eyes on!
I raised Popo, but on
the island where I live,
there's an entire flock
of birds just like him
living in the wild.
Now that you mention it, I think
I've heard of those birds.
On one of Clarines'
southern islands,
the people live and work
side by side with them.
Wait, then are you
from that island?
Yes. My family has been
there for four generations.
All the birds we live with are
the same species as my Popo.
When they spread their
blue- green wings,
they're magnificent!
It looks like the
whole sea is flying!
The birds hear everything from
up in the sky to under the sea,
and by listening to the
sound of the waves,
they can find the mineral
ores near the island.
They even know where
schools of fish are,
so we're always together
when we go out on the ocean!
Here's the mineral ore from
the sea, the walnut stone.
Look how shiny it is
once it's polished!
That's the whistle I heard!
Yes. The birds are
why I've come.
Our island is part
of another territory.
A year and a half ago, a new
lord inherited the lands.
He brought some of his
noble friends to visit.
And they hunted all the
birds they could find.
[SHIRAYUKI]
That's horrible.
[KIHAL]
I know. His friends loved it.
The birds' feathers
are very rare,
so they thought they could
get rich selling them.
I can't even think about
it without feeling sick.
[OBI]
Uh?
Once, they even targeted
Popo during a hunt,
and they almost killed him.
We've pleaded with them
so many times to stop.
But they just keep shooting.
The lord told us we needed to
go talk to the prince about it.
That maybe he would care enough
to give us the time of day.
But I have a feeling,
even if I ask him,
he won't do anything, either.
He'll probably just laugh at me.
Those higher classes do like
to look down on folks like us.
So you know,
that's not how I would describe
Prince Zen's character at all.
[KIHAL] Uh? Uh... Wait.
No, I don't believe you!
He's nobility, royalty,
even! He has to be awful.
But he's not.
[KIHAL]
Uh?
I'm very sorry.
It's just that everyone
is counting on me.
But, I'm not even
sure what to say.
[sniffs] I-I didn't
mean to bother you.
You didn't, but I
have to get back.
[KIHAL] Can I stay here until
I meet with the prince?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Of course.
[whistling]
[ZEN] I understand what
you're asking of me.
If I would make bird
hunting illegal,
and make Yuris Island
a nature reserve.
[KIHAL]
Yes, sir.
[ZEN] I'll consider it.
Expect my decision tomorrow.
However, weighing the evidence,
I believe this should
be discussed
and settled among
the concerned parties,
Lord Brecker of Yuris Island,
and its resident, Kihal Toghrul.
[KIHAL]
Mm.
[BRECKER laughs]
Pardon my amusement.
Your Highness, I do not
wish to waste your time
with such a trivial matter.
We understand each other
now, don't we, Toghrul?
Miss Kihal, a room
is prepared for you.
Please, make yourself at home.
[footsteps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
What did he say?
That the parties concerned
should discuss it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I see.
[OBI] Worrying about this
isn't gonna do you any good.
Some herbs are protected
because of their unique
and special benefits.
Maybe the birds have something
equally special to offer.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[MITSUHIDE] Even if the birds
are important to the residents
of the island, the lord
obviously doesn't care.
For him, it's all about hunting
with his rich friends on
his land. End of story.
The island's mineral
ore is walnut stone.
Unfortunately, it's
not worth very much.
My hands are tied.
This is well within the lord's
rights, he and I both know it.
[KIKI] Hold on. What is this
trinket Lord Brecker brought?
[ZEN] Oh. It's a decorative
arrow souvenir.
He never thinks to
question himself.
Men like that believe
their opinions
should just be accepted as fact.
[MITSUHIDE]
I'm curious,
why did the viscount bring
this to you in the first place?
[ZEN] Probably as a gesture of
good will and a formal greeting.
I'd never met him before today.
Uh-oh.
I hate to say it, but
you're being used, Zen.
Oh, just shut up.
Yeah, shut up.
Uh! Aren't you supposed
to back me up here, Kiki?
[ZEN]
All right, enough.
The point is, I wish I
could help that girl.
What the lord's been
doing is simply wrong.
[OBI]
May we enter?
[ZEN]
Shirayuki?
Zen, there's something
I'd like to ask.
So, Kihal, is it true that
with one whistle signal,
the bird will fly in any
direction you choose?
[KIHAL]
Yes, sir.
Everyone who has trained on the
island can do the same thing.
[ZEN] Can you send
it a great distance?
Certainly.
We often send them out to
fishing boats on the open water.
How do they know
where the boats are?
[KIHAL]
We use this.
[ZEN]
A bell?
[KIHAL]
Right.
These ones made
from walnut stones
each have their
own unique sound.
The birds can detect
the slightest nuance
in tone from bell to bell.
If they hear the ring
of the bell in advance,
they will land wherever they
hear that sound coming from.
Fascinating.
If at all possible,
I may want to use them as
a means of communication.
[KIHAL] Uh! Why would
you need that here?
[ZEN] Because of
another little birdie.
She said the ability
to control them
could have other
positive applications.
So I figured, if we can use
them for communication,
it would benefit the
kingdom in a new way.
It's definitely
worth investigating.
Let's test it over
a long distance.
Are you willing to help me?
Why a test?
Well, I'd like to see for
myself how well it works.
You mean, at the castle?
[ZEN]
That's right. Tomorrow evening.
I'll do it.
May I choose an assistant
to ring the bell, though?
Yes, I suppose that's fine.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What?! I have to ring it?
Please, I'm begging you!
I know this is asking a lot,
but right now the castle still
seems like it's my enemy!
[SHIRAYUKI]
What do you mean by that?
I realize this was
the prince's idea,
but I still don't
really trust him yet.
Since you seem to have
so much faith in him,
then I would rather
work with you first,
so maybe I can learn
to trust him!
Okay, if you think that'll help!
[gasps] Oh, thank you!
Thank you, Shirayuki!
[OBI]
Heh.
[ZEN] The test will
proceed as follows:
The bird will be sent
bearing a document,
to a point ten kilometers
west of the castle,
at a lakeside watchtower
that would normally take
40 minutes, if by horse.
The assistant at the watchtower
will receive the document,
sign it, attach the bell,
and send the bird
back to the castle.
This must all occur within
no more than 25 minutes.
If all conditions are met,
then we've succeeded.
If not, this test will be
considered a failure.
To complete that whole
distance in only 25 minutes?
But it's only to the watchtower.
It's not just there, it's
there and back, moron.
[ZEN] The bird handler
will be Kihal Toghrul.
Shirayuki will assist her.
Only three soldiers and a
messenger will accompany her
to the watchtower.
That is all.
[BRECKER] Hm? The little
apple-haired urchin?
[laughs] That's adorable.
I was wondering why
something so ridiculous
was brought up out of
the clear, blue sky.
You got the prince's
friend on your team, huh?
Clever girl you are, Toghrul.
The prince's friend?!
What are you implying?!
[ZEN]
Lord Brecker.
Right now, we have
only one goal,
to see if these birds
can benefit Clarines.
I would like for you to
judge this objectively,
as a lord of this kingdom.
Hm?
Very well, Highness,
but I think it's only fair
that I accompany them to the
lakeside watchtower, as well.
For I myself am not suspicious,
but if those girls behave
dishonestly in any way,
then it would reflect
poorly on you.
[KIHAL growls]
[gasps]
[ZEN]
So be it.
Lord Brecker, Shirayuki,
and the others
will head to the
lakeside watchtower.
The bird will be sent
at four o'clock,
and the test will begin.
[KIHAL]
Shirayuki!
[bell rings]
This is your special
sound, Popo.
I'll be waiting.
Good luck!
Thanks.
Almost deadline.
Yeah. Shirayuki should be
waiting at the lake by now.
It's time, Kihal. Are you ready?
Yes.
[bell tolls]
[ZEN]
Let the test begin, now!
Make me proud, Popo.
Shirayuki's waiting, so fly!
[whistling]
Such a clear sound.
Shall we venture outside
to wait now, Miss?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Sure!
Uh! Lord Brecker?
[BRECKER]
Spectacular view.
I enjoy high places
that boast a vista.
There are some things
people far below
are simply incapable of seeing.
[BRECKER]
Young Shirayuki.
I'd like to strike a
deal with you, my dear.
What?
[BRECKER] I've heard a bit
about you here and there.
I understand you're an
apprentice at the castle?
Even though you're the prince's
friend, you're still a commoner,
so you'll never have
access to certain amenities.
For example, parties that
nobles attend are off limits,
because you'll never
be seen as elite.
Due to this, not even Prince Zen
can continue
fraternizing with you.
But I can offer you my support
while under deep cover,
of course.
In exchange, I want you to
make sure this test fails.
That's if the bird
actually makes it here.
He will make it!
[gasps] Are you spurning
my generous offer?!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes, you bet I am!
It's very important that
this test goes well!
[growls] Bad news,
it's not going to!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
You hateful man!
The bell's gone!
[BRECKER] Stay in there
until time runs out!
[SHIRAYUKI groaning]
What are you doing?!
This is against the rules!
Stand down!
How dare a lowly soldier like
you question a Lord's choice?
[SHIRAYUKI] Lord Brecker!
Let me out, please!
[BRECKER] Listen, brat!
I stand to lose it all
if that sappy do-gooder
convinces the prince
that these birds have anything
more to offer than feathers!
I'm not blind. I see what
you're trying to do,
and I'm going to ensure you
don't get away with it!
I will not be made a fool of!
[SOLDIER C]
Huh?
[OBI] That's quite a
commotion up there.
I'll go check it out.
It doesn't take too much
to shut you down, I see.
And another thing, girl!
Don't bother whining to
the prince about this!
The truth is he can't afford to
take the word of a rube like you
over that of an esteemed subject
and risk causing
his kingdom strife.
Sadly, having no social
status usually comes
with painful realities.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I suppose you're right.
Zen will always be a prince,
and there will always be
rules he'll have to follow.
But that doesn't matter.
I still have to try to
do the right thing here,
no matter what it might cost me!
[BRECKER growls] Rubbish!
You have no power, girl!
[SHIRAYUKI]
You're wrong.
True human value can't be
measured by social status,
it's measured by one's
depth of character.
Meanwhile, you've shown you
have no character at all!
[splash]
[gasps] No!
[gasps]
[OBI]
I'm coming, Miss!
You lunatic, what are
you trying to do?!
The bell got thrown
into the lake!
If we don't find it and ring
it, Popo won't land here.
[OBI] The viscount
did this, didn't he?
That girl jumped from
this height and survived?
[SHIKITO]
You're under arrest.
Effective immediately,
Lord Brecker.
Then you're choosing to side
with that red-headed peasant.
What she says is indisputable.
Prince Zen won't be
convinced otherwise.
And, honestly, neither
will anyone else.
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's Popo!
Wait! It's flying away!
Hey, the bell! Where do
you think it landed?
Not too far away from
where I jumped in!
Only ten minutes left.
And there's no sign
of the bird anywhere.
[KIHAL]
Come on. Please, hurry.
[gasps]
[OBI gasps]
Any luck?
No, I can't find it!
[SOLDIER C]
Shirayuki, look!
[SHIRAYUKI]
There he is!
[OBI]
He came back around!
What is he trying to do?
[gasps]
[KIHAL]
The birds hear everything
from up in the sky
to under the sea,
and by listening to
the sound of the waves,
they can find the mineral
ores near the island.
Two more minutes
before time runs out, sir.
It's been almost 25 minutes.
This test might not
succeed after all.
[SOLDIER G] To make a bird
fly with just a sound...
Quiet, all of you.
I cannot hear the wings.
Uh.
[whistling]
[KIHAL]
Welcome back, Popo!
[ALL gasp]
[KIHAL]
Your highness.
The document and the bell!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
I have confirmed each of
the signatures as valid.
I can find no fault with it.
Then...
Clarines will now
use bird handlers
as a means of communication!
[gasps] Popo!
[POPO chirps]
Thank you so much, Shirayuki!
Your highness.
What is it?
There is a report
with the signatures.
[gasps]
[ZEN] Mitsuhide, Kiki!
Ready the horses!
[BOTH]
Uh!
[SHIKITO] "The viscount
tried to sabotage the test,
so I had to arrest him.
He is out of the picture.
Unfortunately, the
assistant was injured."
[galloping]
Your highness! If I may, sir.
I can tell you everything.
[HARUKA] When the viscount
asked to accompany the group
up to the watchtower,
I presumed Prince Zen would
outright refuse that request,
and yet he dared to allow it.
What do you mean, he dared?
Well, it seemed to
be fairly obvious.
The viscount was planning
to use Shirayuki
for his personal advancement
and financial gain.
He truly must have trusted
that girl and our soldiers
to have left it to them.
However, when the time comes,
how will he protect
what's important?
I doubt he's figured
that part out yet.
[ZEN]
I see. Thank you.
Please look after my
horse. I'll be back.
Master, Shirayuki is upstairs.
[SHIKITO] Then I heard
Shirayuki say:
There will always be rules
you have to follow,
whether you
like it or not.
She'd try to do
the right thing,
no matter what it cost her.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
Zen!
[ZEN]
Show me where you're hurt.
Zen, I, uh, sorry...
Wait. I'm not... I mean,
it's not like I was ever gonna
try to hide this from you.
I know how mad you'd be at me.
Idiot.
[ZEN gasps]
[MITSUHIDE]
To find out what happened
between you and Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI] Be calm. No one's
gonna notice anything's weird.
[MITSUHIDE]
What's going on?
[SHIRAYUKI]
I should take some time
to really figure out
how I feel about Zen.
[OBI] Don't worry, Miss.
He's on his way.