[SHIRAYUKI]
It must be cold
because we're so close
to the mountains.
[KIKI] Yes, this place is a
far cry from sunny Clarines.
[MITSUHIDE] I wish we
could take you all the way.
We do feel guilty about that,
but we need to get
to Laxdo quickly.
There's no reason
to feel guilty.
I'm just happy you're
taking me as far as you can.
I can't believe they sent
you all the way to Laxdo.
Seems like being a court
herbalist is hard work.
I'm grateful for it, though.
Plus, I like that I get to
spend so much time outside.
By the way, we told Lord Haruka
that you'd been granted a
position inside the castle.
He said "congratulations",
right?
[MITSUHIDE] Yeah, but the
sarcasm was palpable.
[KIKI]
He's interesting.
He can't hide what
he's thinking,
so it's funny when he tries.
[MITSUHIDE]
Yeah, that's true.
Zen. Why the big hurry?
Is there something wrong?
Well, it is a routine
fort inspection.
But we're a little worried
since we haven't heard
from them in a while.
I suppose this is where
we all part for now!
Are you sure you'll be
all right in this cold?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yeah!
[ZEN]
See you soon.
[horse whinnies]
[ZEN] We can learn so
much from the outside.
Wait!
Take care of yourself!
[ZEN] Experiencing this
country in a new way.
Encounters with people
that make this land home.
Discovering feelings
we never knew existed.
It's strange that no one
seems to be on watch.
Hey! Is anyone there?
We're from the
royal guard. Hello?
Be right there!
[panting, yelps]
[MITSUHIDE]
Whoa, easy there.
[SHUKA gasps]
You're all here.
Your Highness came, too?
We haven't been getting
routine reports.
I grew concerned.
You have to leave!
[OBI]
Master!
[ZEN, MITSUHIDE]
Uh.
[SHUKA yelps]
It looks like everyone
inside the fort is asleep.
Asleep?
Um, I've never seen you before.
I'm Obi, the prince's attendant!
Not quite. Your trial
period isn't over.
Come, on. How much longer
am I gonna have to keep
proving my loyalty to you?
[ZEN] For as long as
it takes. I'm going in.
[gasps] Wait! You can't!
The entire place
has been possessed
by some kind of evil spirit!
Evil spirit?
[SHUKA] It started
about three weeks ago.
One by one all the men
began feeling strange.
They said their limbs
felt weak and heavy
and that their
vision was blurry.
Everyone started getting
dizzy and losing their balance.
We called a doctor to help, but
he ended up falling sick, too.
We couldn't
pinpoint a cause,
so it's gotta be the work
of some evil spirit.
Are you ill?
I feel better than anyone
else around here.
But still,
I was in no shape to venture
out in search of more help.
[ZEN] I'd like to go in
and take a look around.
[OBI gasps]
No, you can't!
If it's contagious,
you'll get sick!
I've been exposed already,
but... I'll be careful.
Get some rest, you've earned it.
We'll take over from here.
[whimpers] Yes, sir.
Zen. You should try to
get back out by sunset.
[ZEN]
Right.
Mitsuhide, don't let
anyone else in.
I want to keep
contact to a minimum.
Of course, sir.
[OBI]
Please, Master,
do you really think going
in there is the best idea?
There's just too much at risk!
I'm willing to take that
chance at this point.
These soldiers need us
to find a solution.
We can't stop him?
This is crazy!
He'd do anything
for his soldiers.
Hold on a second.
Why aren't you advising him?
That's your job, isn't it?
[MITSUHIDE]
Yes. That is my job.
[OBI]
Hm...
[ZEN] Nothing in here seems
out of the ordinary to me.
[OBI] What if the illness really
is the work of some evil spirit?
You believe in
that kind of thing?
I'd rather fight ghosts
than a disease.
[OBI]
Uh...
[KIKI]
This must be the armory.
I don't see why it would
be affec... ted...
Oh.
You mean it was empty?
[OBI] Yes, and I'm
pretty sure that boy
didn't know anything about it.
There were claw marks, too.
Someone used that illness as
a chance to rob the place.
Shall we shift our focus
to hunting bandits?
That's my specialty, you know.
[ZEN]
Put those away. Right now...
A specialty?
What if we brought Shirayuki?
She could have some insight
about what's causing the
soldiers to get sick.
Not to mention healing them.
Go get her.
[MITSUHIDE]
Right!
[KIKI] I hope he gets back
with her before night fall.
Hey, uh, Miss Kiki?
Is Mitsuhide afraid
of stating his opinion
around the prince
for some reason?
I've noticed that you
speak your mind
when you think it's important,
but Mitsuhide seems
go easy on him.
Huh. I wonder.
They're back.
[OBI]
Hm?
[SHIRAYUKI] Did you follow
the doctor's orders exactly?
[SHUKA]
Yes, as much as we could.
But there aren't enough
plants this time of year
to get everyone the
treatment they need.
[ZEN]
Wait, what do you mean?
Cold weather affects potency.
It weakens most herbs,
so you have to use more
to make them work.
Huh.
[SHIRAYUKI] There.
Anything else you remember?
No.
I was usually on watch outside,
so that's all I really know.
I hate that I can't
be more help.
Oh, no, please
don't feel bad!
I won't rest until
these men are well!
I'm Shuka. Just let me
know what I can do.
You've done so
much already.
Right now, you need
to take it easy.
[SHUKA sighs]
Sure.
I think he's worse than
he was when we got here.
Zen, you have to get
some fresh air.
I'm worried about you.
I'll be all right.
Did you hear a word
that I just said?!
[ZEN] I don't like to
be outside in the cold!
Quit making excuses!
I can't leave you alone after
bringing you into this mess!
If you could help me
now, I'd let you stay.
You must know I want
you here with me.
But you can't get sick!
You should go.
I'll do everything I can
to help these men.
I won't get sick.
It's fine. I'll stay.
[MITSUHIDE]
Zen.
Uh?
You told Kiki you'd
be out by sunset.
As prince, it's your
duty to stay healthy.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh!
[ZEN] I was being
selfish. Forgive me.
Let me know if anything changes.
[footsteps]
[MITSUHIDE]
I was impressed back there.
You let logic win over
your stubbornness.
[ZEN]
You were right. Again.
No need to sulk about it.
I understand that you're just
concerned about Shirayuki.
But you really should trust her.
She knows what
she's doing in there.
[ZEN]
I know.
On an entirely
different note,
I didn't know you were so
sensitive to the cold!
Are you sure you should be
lying down in the snow?
[grunts]
[ZEN] Leave me alone!
That's not what I meant!
Did the prince actually
listen to him just now?
Why does that surprise you?
This is what usually happens.
He only ever listens
to Mitsuhide.
Which must be because
he keeps his mouth shut
unless it's important.
That way the Prince
will take him seriously.
[sighs]
[SHUKA] Hello, Shirayuki! I was
just coming to check on you.
Are you sure you've
gotten enough rest?
As much as I could under
the circumstances.
Good. I haven't determined
the source yet.
But it seems like the
symptoms are changing.
It isn't progressing the way
something like this should be.
What would cause that to happen?
[SHIRAYUKI] That's what
I'm trying to figure out.
In the meantime,
I finally found the medicine
the physician was using.
I plan to try mixing a few
other ingredients with it.
[gasps]
[SHUKA] Ah! Hey, Shirayuki!
Are you all right?
Oh, no. Why is it
coming on so quickly?
Maybe it varies per person?
I wouldn't know.
[gasps] Wait a second.
Shuka, you said you spent a
lot of time outside on watch,
didn't you?
Um. Yes.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Then that means the source
must be something in this room.
[SHIRAYUKI]
The closer they are to the fire,
the worse their symptoms are.
It's really cold
out here tonight.
[ZEN]
Indeed.
[door opens]
[SHIRAYUKI panting]
[ZEN]
Shirayuki? What's wrong?
Oh, don't worry.
I've just been too
close to the fire.
That's the source.
It's coming from the wood.
[ZEN, MITSUHIDE gasp]
[SHIRAYUKI] Burning it
releases harmful particles.
Particles that are
toxic to breathe.
They cause the same
symptoms, too.
[ZEN] Where did
the logs come from?
[SHIRAYUKI]
From a band of travelers.
That's what Shuka said.
They left them here at no cost
because they were
too heavy to carry.
[SHUKA]
Your Highness, I'm so sorry!
Don't worry. Are you
feeling better, at least?
[SHUKA] Uh. Yes! The medicine
Shirayuki gave me did wonders!
Thank goodness.
I'm so relieved that it worked.
[ZEN gasps]
You should go.
I'll do everything I
can to help these men.
[ZEN exhales]
[gasps]
[ZEN]
You win.
I guess it's official.
You're amazing.
What?
Would you mind staying
here for a few more days?
I'd like for you to nurse
the soldiers back to health.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes!
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[KIKI] It's amazing
they're so much better
after just a few days.
I knew Shirayuki
could handle this.
Yeah.
[MITSUHIDE]
Zen.
[ZEN]
Bandits?
Apparently there's a group
of them in the area.
They're using Laxdo
as their base.
So did you find their hide out?
I need a bit more time, but I
have an idea where they are.
Why don't you three let
me find them for you?
It's like I told you before.
Hunting bandits is my specialty!
I swear he's part monkey.
He certainly smells like one.
[ZEN]
Kiki, Mitsuhide.
I think the four of us
need to take care of
the bandits on our own.
We probably shouldn't
keep relying on Shirayuki
to save the day.
[grunting, sighs]
So, what are you making now?
[SHIRAYUKI] An infusion of
medicinal herbs, wanna try?
Medicine always
makes me throw up!
[laughs] It doesn't
taste bad at all.
No, thanks. Hey, Shirayuki?
I have something to tell you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
Thank you for always
being so nice to me.
And there's something else.
Do you think Zen is
embarrassed of this outpost?
[SHIRAYUKI] What would
make you think that?
[SHUKA] I feel like we've
disappointed him.
I'm scared that he won't visit
us as often because of it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Does Zen come here a lot?
[SHUKA] Yes, and he spends
time with us on his visits.
He goes out on patrols, listens
to the old soldiers' stories.
He even talks to
apprentices like me
and actually seems to enjoy it.
We count the days till he comes.
I really hope he still wants
to see us after all this.
[SHIRAYUKI] I don't think you
should worry about it.
[SHUKA]
Uh?
Zen doesn't abandon people.
His visits mean that he cares.
You should know a little illness
would never change him.
He may even come more, now!
[SHIRAYUKI]
All right. Glad that's done!
Now, I just have to write
the report for my records,
check on the medicine,
prepare one more batch,
and then...
--[door opens]
--[ZEN] Shirayuki!
[gasps]
Oh, sorry. Were you asleep?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Of course not!
All right. Thought you'd
like to see your handiwork.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
Hey!
You sure you feel well
enough to be doing that?
Yeah! We're doin' great, now!
So much better.
Although, I think I still need
routine check-ups for a while!
[SOLDIER A] You just want
her to take your pulse!
Wonderful! Prove to her you're
well by going back to work!
[SOLDIER A]
Oh! Your Highness!
[SOLDIER B]
Please pardon us!
See that? They're looking
good, thanks to you.
If you can handle it,
I'll be back soon!
Right, then. I guess I
should start cooking lunch.
[groans]
So tired...
But I'll get rest soon.
[OBI]
Oh, it's Red.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ouch!
That was graceful. I
wonder what's wrong.
I'd help, but the prince
said not to go near her
without his permission.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh?
There goes my job.
Oh! Well, this is
quite a surprise.
What brings you here?
[OBI] I'm currently serving
as Zen's attendant.
Interesting.
I appreciate your help.
I hope that you're
not afraid of me.
[SHIRAYUKI] Why would I
be frightened of someone
who just saved me
from a nasty spill?
That's silly. Bye.
Wait a sec.
You don't seem like
you're feeling very well.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Please don't say anything.
I should tell the prince,
but I won't.
Even though he's
my boss, not you.
Then I suppose I owe you one.
Really?
[OBI] Does this mean
she won't tell him
I'm the one who
shot the arrow?
It's a deal. But why do you
think you need to hide it?
[SOLDIERS laughing]
[OBI] The soldiers seem
to be doing better.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm-hm.
But they might start
feeling bad again
if they're worried about me.
Why do I want to follow her?
[ZEN] You didn't find
anything in the south?
No, but we still have
to survey the grounds
from the western tower.
[SOLDIER C]
Your Highness,
I've organized a patrol
party of able-bodied men.
We await your command.
[ZEN] And the soldiers
are well enough?
Yes, sir. We owe it to
Shirayuki, of course.
Your men are ready to
return to our posts.
We'll prove that we are
worthy of your confidence.
Good to hear.
Well, don't overdo it.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[SOLDIER D] Oh, Shuka, uh, was
there any medicine left over?
No. She only makes enough
for the men on each shift.
I think she's starting
the next batch now.
[ZEN, KIKI]
Uh.
[SOLDIER D]
Oh, all right.
Is everyone still
taking the medicine?
[SHUKA]
Yes, sir.
We're already back up
to three shifts per day.
Right.
And considering each one
is every eight hours...
I'm so blind.
Uh. That's 24 hours.
If she's always working,
then when does Shirayuki
get a chance to sleep?
Uh!
[knocking]
Uh?!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen!
[ZEN]
Have a seat over here.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...? Sure.
I want you to close your
eyes and count to 60.
Huh? Is this a joke?
No, it's not. Close your
eyes and don't open them.
But, what for?
Now!
One!
Ah! Eyes are closed.
[ZEN]
Two... Three...
Your face looks so pale.
Why didn't you say something?
[ZEN]
Mm?
[panting] Hi, Master.
I've got some good news.
[ZEN gasps, grunts]
[BANDITS laughing]
[BANDIT A] Who woulda thought
they'd fall for the firewood?
[BANDIT B] Now, we gotta
find the right buyer.
We could make some good money!
[ZEN]
Thanks for your confession.
I'll consider that
when sentencing you.
[BANDIT J]
Who do you think you are?!
We are soldiers
representing the crown.
You've broken laws.
And unfortunately, we
can't just let that go.
[BANDITS laugh]
Let me get this straight.
We're supposed to believe
you four are soldiers?
[BANDIT D] They brought a
lady to the party for us.
What a thoughtful gift!
Silence. I will not allow
you to insult anyone here.
[BANDITS laugh]
Yeah, what are
you gonna do?!
[ZEN] You're asking the
wrong question, friend.
You should be asking why I'm
taking your theft personally.
Why am I so angry?
Ask me who we must be that
we have no fear of you.
Who I know that you've made
suffer. What am I going to do?
I'm going to be the kind of
person she can believe in.
The kind of person she would
never want to walk away from.
The hell are you
talking about?!
Don't worry about it.
Just needed to get
that off my chest.
You wouldn't understand anyway.
That's enough!
Too slow!
[MITSUHIDE]
Sorry! I was listening to you.
Great speech, huh?
If not a little intense.
A little?
[BANDIT A yells]
Lucky. Wish he'd say
that stuff about me, too!
[BANDIT H groans]
[BANDIT E groans]
[BANDITS groaning]
[door closes]
Did I wake you?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes, but it's fine.
[ZEN] I'm sorry I didn't notice
you weren't feeling well.
I should've seen it. I wasn't
paying close enough attention.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
But next time, please,
say something to me.
We can always work
out a schedule for you
that accommodates
proper rest.
No one needs to handle this
kind of situation alone.
You can trust me, too.
Will you do that?
It's only fair.
Yes, of course I will.
[ZEN] Don't be hard
on yourself, either.
You may be exhausted now,
but that changes nothing.
Everyone here was
saved thanks to you.
I don't believe I've
thanked you, yet.
I'm so grateful you came
to help. Sincerely.
Yes, you came to heal soldiers,
but you also healed me.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
You're an inspiration, and now
I feel like I can move forward.
[SHIRAYUKI]
That's how I feel about you.
You inspire me.
You make me want to be
better. To give more.
[ZEN] I'm counting on you
to be vigilant from now on.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
Bye, Shirayuki!
I'll write to you every day!
I look forward to it!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[ZEN] We can learn so
much from the outside.
Experiencing this
country in a new way.
Chance encounters with all the
people that make this land home.
Discovering feelings
we never knew existed.
These moments are the
lights that never fade.
Greetings, Prince Izana.
Welcome back home.
[IZANA]
Well, hello. Little Brother.
[SHIRAYUKI]
This makes me uncomfortable.
[RAJ]
I can assure you,
I will valiantly attempt
to make her happy.
[SHIRAYUKI] The only thing
I can do is be myself.
[IZANA] Which would make him
an awfully incompetent prince.