So then,
I can go home?
[jingling]
[gasps] Is that...
walnut stone?
From the package Zen sent.
He asked me to include this for
you along with his message.
It's so beautiful.
[KIKI] Apparently, Obi wound up
carrying it around with him.
We can use this
as a signal now
to let Zen know where
they're headed with us.
Don't let him take
full credit, though.
It's a gift from Kihal.
That's so sweet.
So, you said you got them
to put you here on purpose,
which is great and everything...
but what are we supposed
to do out at sea?
To start, we simply
let them sail,
and take us directly
to their base.
[ZEN gasps]
[MITSUHIDE]
Zen!
[ZEN]
I'm on my way, Shirayuki.
[CITIZEN A]
What?! Prince Raj is here?
Right now?
[CITIZEN C]
Why would that idiot prince
even come to the port town?
[CITIZEN B] I don't know. I'm
just tellin' you what I heard!
That brat is such a pain!
You know he's just gonna demand
a bunch of women and wine.
[CITIZEN A]
Heh. You got that right.
[clears throat]
Attention! We're setting out
to pursue the Claw of the Sea!
What?! The Claw of the Sea?
They're violent,
no-good pirates.
They've had their way
with the sea too long.
Right, and from what I heard,
they also force merchant
vessels to pay tolls
if they plan to use
"their" waters.
[CITIZEN B]
That's ridiculous!
[CITIZEN A]
And that's not all.
They'll kidnap people, too,
if they think they'll
fetch a good price.
[CITIZEN B]
Are you serious?
All those who wish
to join can follow me!
This way!
[CITIZEN C]
That's a great story, and all...
But some of us got
cargo we gotta move!
That's right, we
have our own work!
[CITIZEN A] What the hell
is Prince Raj thinking?!
He has to know he's
no match for a pirate!
[CITIZEN C chuckles]
No kidding!
[RAJ] Why are they
just standing around?
We do not have time for this!
[CROWD chattering]
[RAJ growls]
Are you going out there,
Your Highness?
You know they may not take
kindly to orders from you.
[RAJ]
Hmph! Don't underestimate.
[footsteps]
[OFFICIALS gasps]
What?!
It's him!
That's the prince!
That's Prince Raj?
[gasps]
[RAJ] Wow, not encouraging.
Luckily, looks can't kill!
[whimpering]
[ZEN]
Are we clear?
No questions on the
plan or anyone's part?
[MUKAZE] Itoya, round up
our scattered men.
Right.
[ZEN]
Raj.
[RAJ]
Hm?
I know you can do this.
--[whimpering]
--[CROWD chattering]
Listen. I, uh...
I mean, we,
we cannot allow the Claw
of the Sea to escape us!
So please...
I ask you to lend
me your strength.
[MUKAZE] I wonder how Prince Raj
is holding up at the port.
Tanbarun is his kingdom,
and beyond that
we can only trust him and
make sure we do our part.
[MUKAZE]
Here we go.
[MIHAYA]
Prince Zen to the right here.
[PIRATE C] Boss! Three ships
spotted at 12 o'clock!
What? The Lions of the Mountain?
We can't tell who they are yet!
If it is the Lions,
then that precious little red
head might just come in handy.
Shall we find out who they are
by watching their response?
Take her on deck immediately.
[PIRATE C]
Yes, ma'am!
I hope the Lions stay quiet.
That'll make our work
a whole lot easier.
True. But if not, we still
have dear Kazuki...
Even if the girl is
worthless a scream or two
from their pretty boy should
make sure they keep quiet.
[door opens]
[PIRATE C]
Hey, Apple-head. You're up.
[KAZUKI]
What do you want?!
If things start looking
dangerous, just shout for me.
[PIRATE D]
Uh?!
Boss!
Yeah, what's all
the fuss about?
[PIRATE D]
Look. Over there!
Uh?
[gasps]
Well, this is unexpected.
Those aren't Lions at all...
They're merchant ships.
And every last one of 'em
is flying a navy flag.
They're trying to block our way!
[PIRATE C]
Boss! I got the girl for ya.
[bird chirps]
[gasps]
[RAJ]
Sakaki, that's the one.
Yes, Sir.
[CITIZEN B]
Go figure,
those rumors were
wrong about Prince Raj.
Workin' with merchants?
Asking for meager folks like
us to put out our ships?
Yeah. Different from
the last time I saw him.
Less pompous, that's
for damn sure.
What could we do, though?
He asked so directly,
hard to ignore him after that.
[CITIZEN B]
Heh. That's true.
[PIRATE C]
How are there so many?
[PIRATE A]
Do you see at the front!
Isn't that a royal vessel
leading the fleet?
It's royal?
Hey, Boss, what now?
[UMIHEBI]
Just my luck.
[OFFICIAL A] Prince Raj!
We have a confirmed sighting
of Shirayuki aboard
the Claw's vessel!
[RAJ gasps]
Is she all right?
[OFFICIAL A]
Appears to be!
So Shirayuki and Kiki,
as well as the boy Kazuki,
they're all being held as
prisoners aboard that ship.
Sakaki.
Sir?
To be perfectly honest,
I've always considered myself
to be a pitiful prince...
but now that I'm so mad,
I don't feel all that
pitiful anymore.
[SAKAKI]
Uh...
[RAJ]
Pirates! Can you hear me?!
[SHIRAYUKI, PIRATE C gasps]
[RAJ] I am the first prince
of Tanbarun, Raj Schenazade!
The redheaded girl you've
taken is special!
In Tanbarun, she is
held in high regard!
The only person to hold the
title "Friend of the Crown"!
Understand that we will not
allow you to get away from us!
[gasps] A title?
There's a "Friend of the Crown,"
and it's this girlie?!
What the hell?
So, the Prince of Tanbarun
was after her, not the
Lions of the Mountain?
Damn it.
There's no way we can
take on that many ships!
Retreat! Quickly!
Slip away to the west!
[PIRATES]
Aye-aye!
"Friend of the Crown"?
That's the first I've
heard of such a title.
And when was this decided?
Just now, in fact.
I thought it would
make them nervous.
[SAKAKI]
Hm...
[RAJ]
Uh! I mean. It's true, though.
Well, congratulations,
Your Highness.
Whaddaya think you're doing
showing your face! Huh?
I see Prince Raj.
[UMIHEBI] Might want to head
back below deck, dearie.
Oh, no, what happened
to your face?
Did Umihebi do that to you?
She did. But I'll be fine.
[KAZUKI]
Those bastards!
[exhales]
[SHIRAYUKI] It's anyone's
guess what they'll do to us.
I can't let my guard down.
I heard her command them to
turn and escape to the west.
Ships were approaching
from the bow?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes.
[PIRATE B] The royal vessels
are coming after us!
Quit your bellyachin',
and man up!
We're almost to the
Blue Vortex, boys...
They can't follow us there,
no matter how hard they try.
We just have to stay
on top of 'em, now.
But look at this...
Hey! What's that?!
A bad omen.
Uh! It's too late!
[CITIZEN A]
All hands on deck!
We're too close
to the maelstrom!
Will someone cut the rudder?
Now! As in right now!
We're getting sucked in!
It's no use, Your Highness!
We can't move in any closer!
We can't?! Tell me why!
It's the Blue Vortex!
Uh!
[SAKAKI]
A cluster of maelstroms
that randomly appears
in Tanbarun's seas.
Unless one knows the
currents inside and out,
it's impossible to traverse.
If we simply plunged in,
the ship would be
smashed to splinters!
[whimpering]
[SHIRAYUKI screams]
[KAZUKI groaning]
[UMIHEBI] I bet that landlubber
prince isn't much for swimming.
This'll shake him.
I think this ought
to be far enough.
It wasn't a part of my plan,
but at least we can
hide out for a while.
[CREW groaning]
So, uh, are we gonna make it?!
Because this ship sure
is rocking a lot!
Didn't I did say we
shouldn't just plunge in?
Oh, shut up! I know
you saw it, too!
That stupid pirate
lady sneered at me!
How can a person
look that arrogant
while they're retreating?
Are you even listening, Sakaki?
Sire, I just remembered.
The Blue Vortex will shift.
It changes direction
every ten seconds.
If we go with the current
instead of against it,
then maybe...
Every ten seconds?
[RAJ]
Hm...
So, any idea when we
should start counting
for the next shift change?
[SAKAKI]
No.
[RAJ whimpers]
Listen up, men! Move the
rudder left and right!
That should get us past
this vortex to calm waters!
[CREW]
Yes, sir!
[RAJ]
Left!
[CREW]
[RAJ]
Right!
[CREW]
Yes.
You were just making
random things up,
weren't you, Prince?
At times like this,
it's sink or swim.
[retches]
[RAJ]
Don't underestimate Tanbarun...
Where are we?
Pretty sure the Claw
of the Sea's base.
I don't know the exact
location, though.
We always came in
off the water.
[UMIHEBI] Aw... What a
shame, my darling Red!
No one will be coming to save
you as long as you're here.
[PIRATES chuckle]
[SHIRAYUKI growls]
[PIRATE C]
Heh.
Now then, it's time
to seriously consider
what lucky buyer gets
to purchase you from me.
[PIRATE C]
Hey, Boss!
[UMIHEBI]
Uh?
Sorry, but they
followed us somehow!
[UMIHEBI]
They what?
Oh, come on, you've
got to be kidding me!
We did it.
We caught up with
them, Highness.
Yes, we did.
Thank you for your hard work!
Without all of you, we
would have never survived!
[SAKAKI]
Being swallowed up was, in fact,
the correct course of action.
[RAJ]
Ah-hem. However.
I'm afraid I must ask
for your help again!
Forward ho, brave gentlemen!
Destroy the pirate ship and cut
off their escape route at once!
[CREW cheers]
Do not falter!
[RAJ screams]
Are you all right, Prince?
Of course I am. Just...
a little terrified.
[KIKI]
You two. Get inside!
Oh. I don't think so!
[SHIRAYUKI screams]
Shirayuki!
[PIRATE C yells]
[MITSUHIDE]
Kiki!
[PIRATE C groans]
[PIRATE D]
I got her! Ah!
A bit of advice. You should
leave my partner alone.
[UMIHEBI]
And who in blazes are you?!
Stop there, or else!
Let go of Shirayuki...
Believe me, I am not one
you want to trifle with!
And what do you plan to
do if I don't let her go?
You must want this redheaded
wonder pretty badly, kid.
You did smash your ship to
get to her. How romantic.
[UMIHEBI grunts]
How dare you?!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi!
[OBI]
Master. Shirayuki. Go inside.
[UMIHEBI]
Not so fast!
You must be Kazuki.
[KAZUKI]
Uh. Yeah.
[ZEN]
Come with us, and move quickly.
[UMIHEBI grunts]
[PIRATE C]
Boss, you okay?!
No! Stop those brats, now!
[PIRATE C groans]
Oh? What's wrong, Umihebi?
You look rather flustered.
[UMIHEBI gasps]
Are you worried
about your castle
on the other side of this cave?
Don't be, we've already
paid it a visit.
Damn Lions. You'll pay!
[PIRATES, LIONS yelling]
Hold on. The Lions
are here, too?
Yes, their chief, Itoya,
and the rest are here.
So you're working together?!
I have to go back out there.
See you later, Shirayuki!
Wait!
[ZEN]
I wasn't ready for this.
I just... I didn't think we'd
be alone together so soon.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[ZEN]
Shirayuki, say something.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen...
[ZEN gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI cries]
Zen... Zen!
[ZEN] I'm sorry it took me
so long to get to you.
[ZEN] There are guards
stationed up above.
You will be safe there.
What about you?
I've got some havoc to
wreak with everyone, so,
wait for me.
[PIRATES groaning]
[PIRATE H yelps]
[MUKAZE grunts]
No!
[MUKAZE]
Tell me.
How does it feel to
be thoroughly tamed,
Claw of the Sea?
And you tell me, what abyss
did you crawl out of?!
[ZEN] A bit overconfident,
don't you think?
You summoned us here. We came
a long way for you, too.
Now, then.
I am the Second Prince of
Clarines, Prince Zen Wisteria.
Do you care to take
me on, filthy pirates?
[growls] Do you care to die?!
[PIRATES yell]
[PIRATES groaning]
[UMIHEBI growls]
Why don't you just
surrender, Umihebi?
Listen, handsome,
I don't know if you're some
sort of royal guard or what,
but you sure as hell keep
getting in my damn way!
Now, back off!
[grunts]
[MUKAZE]
Apologies.
I have a tendency to let
you slip off the hook
at the very last minute.
Not this time,
the day has come to haul
this catch up on shore.
No.
Damn you!
I promise, you don't have
to worry about them.
[door opens]
[gasps]
I've got good news.
It's over.
I can't believe it.
Thank you. Thank
you all so much.
Mihaya, wait out front
for Raj's soldiers.
He should have ordered them
to meet up with us here.
[MIHAYA]
Right.
Zen.
Obi?
Where is he?
[ZEN]
Obi's still down there...
The Claw is in custody.
At this point, they'll
be escorted back.
I imagine Tanbarun will
take care of it from here.
[MUKAZE]
Hey, Kazuki!
Quit pushing! Stop that!
Are you even listening?
[ZEN]
What are you doing, old man?
[MUKAZE chuckles]
I... uh...
You're, uh...
More than welcome to
rest at our village
before heading all the
way back to the castle.
I... I'd like to make it
up to you for everything.
Heh.
[gasps] You!
[MUKAZE]
Mm?
[SHIRAYUKI]
You're my father!
[OBI] I'm sorry.
My job was to guard you.
I'm ashamed of
what I let happen.
[MITSUHIDE]
Got any idea where Obi went?
[KAZUKI]
I was wondering,
do you think maybe you would
want to live with us here?
[OBI]
Forgive me.