[knocking]
Master Obi.
A letter just arrived for you
from Prince Zen of Clarines.
It's marked as urgent.
From Zen?
[OBI]
You can't go.
It's not safe for you to attend.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Mihaya discovered
new information.
Apparently the boy who was
looking for you has a companion,
and they know you're
here at this castle.
Mihaya said they're
coming for you.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Shirayuki!
Found you!
[OBI, SHIRAYUKI]
No.
It's the boy!
[KAZUKI]
Uh? [chuckles]
While I am in fact a boy,
both of you stating the obvious
at the same time
is a bit creepy.
Who the hell are you?
You're the one they
call Kazuki, right?
So you've heard of me.
How flattering.
Oh, I'd love to introduce
myself now, but we have to go.
[ITOYA grunts]
Get out of here!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi!
Someone, help!
Let go of me!
Sorry. I need you to stay still.
[BOTH grunting]
You some sort of special guard?
[OBI]
Who knows?
That guy's holding his
own against Itoya.
If he's from the castle,
we have to leave him here!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Help us!
[OBI]
Move!
[ITOYA groans]
Shirayuki?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm.
Uh?
[ITOYA grunts]
[OBI groans]
[ITOYA]
Sorry about that.
[OBI]
Yeah. I bet.
No, Obi, no!
[SHIRAYUKI panting]
Obi!
Obi! Uh?
[gasps]
This can't be helped.
You'll just be out
for a little while.
I don't know what to do.
Tell me what to do, Eugena.
Shirayuki's gone.
[EUGENA]
Guards! Guards, help!
Guards!
[RAJ whimpering]
Sakaki! Hasn't anyone
located Shirayuki, yet?!
No.
We're continuing to search,
sir, but it's growing late.
The king is being
updated, as well.
Perhaps you could get some rest?
Even if I could sleep,
I'd only have nightmares!
Ah!
She was just with me!
She looked like she was
having a good time, too.
Uh! Tell me why?!
And Prince Zen.
I'll never be able
to apologize enough.
I should...
I should be helping them
look for her now.
No, Your Highness.
Sending the elite
soldiers guarding you
to look for her would be wiser.
[RAJ gasps]
Mister Obi?
Can you hear me, sir?
Are you all right?
[OBI groaning]
You woke up!
[gasps]
Where's Shirayuki?
She's not here.
Those guys took her.
The guards tried to follow them,
but... but in the forest,
they just disappeared.
The guards are still
looking for her, though.
[gasping]
[EUGENA]
They cancelled the ball.
I'm so sorry.
If we hadn't distracted you,
those guys would've
been stopped.
This is our fault.
No, don't feel guilty.
You were only trying to help.
Now, then. Tell me
how long I was out.
Just about an hour.
Listen Obi, you really should
take it easy for a while.
What about arrivals?
Anyone from Clarines?
No, I haven't heard anything.
Would you like me
to check for you?
Yes, please do, and thank you.
[MAID A]
Of course, sir.
It's all right. Shirayuki
will come back to us.
Do you promise?
Cross my heart.
[gasps]
It's already late for you two.
Better go to bed
and get some rest.
[EUGENA, RONA]
Okay.
[OBI] Master and the others
should already be on their way.
When will they get here?
Oh, right.
This was for Shirayuki.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki...
[violin plays]
[SAKAKI] You still haven't
gone to bed, Highness?
What is that piece?
It's the dance I had
arranged for Shirayuki.
Right about now,
we'd have danced.
Shirayuki is the only one
who takes me seriously.
She's always honest, too.
In fact, sometimes,
she's a little too honest.
I haven't been able to
reciprocate anything.
She's done so much,
but I couldn't even protect
her in my own damn castle.
[SAKAKI]
There is still time.
You underestimate yourself.
Surely there must be something
only you can do for her.
Wouldn't you agree?
[OBI]
Miss!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Come in!
[OBI]
Interesting.
Connecting rooms.
Well, that's convenient.
Let me know if you need
anything. I'm right there.
And I'm here!
[OBI grunts]
I still don't understand why
I had to come along
with these people.
You had to "come along
with these people"
in order to help them
find the Kazuki boy.
Yeah, whatever.
[gasps]
[KIKI]
A lot of fires burning tonight.
[ZEN]
I see that.
Faster!
Here from Clarines.
I am Zen Wisteria.
We have been expecting you.
Welcome, Prince Zen.
It is as I said in my message.
I'd like to see
Shirayuki immediately.
About that.
[gasps]
Thank you for seeing me,
Prince Raj. Let's talk.
[RAJ]
Um, right, and I, uh...
Thank you, for coming
all this way, as well.
I mean, like, thank you, too.
[ZEN] Sakaki has already
updated me on Shirayuki.
[gasps] Oh. He has?
Right. Of course
he would have, eh?
[ZEN]
My apologies.
[RAJ]
Uh?
I had heard extremely
concerning reports of people
after Shirayuki, but I had only
investigated them in Clarines.
I should have also
told you about it.
No, Zen. I am the one here
who should be apologizing.
Please, forgive me.
She was my guest and
my responsibility.
[gasps]
[SAKAKI]
Uh.
[ZEN]
So tell me.
Did Shirayuki at least spend
her days here pleasantly?
[RAJ]
I think so. She seemed happy.
Most of her time was spent
doing what interested her.
[ZEN]
Did she smile?
[RAJ]
Mm.
That's wonderful.
[gasps]
[ZEN] Raj, I would like
to act immediately.
May I see Obi if
at all possible?
He's the one who
accompanied Shirayuki.
[door creaks]
[MAID A]
Excuse me!
Apologies for the interruption,
but it's important!
[RAJ]
Obi's disappeared?!
[MAID A] Yes, he said he
wanted to rest until morning,
but when I went to
check on him earlier,
he was nowhere to be found.
Has Obi been made aware
of what's happened?
Yes, sir. I told him
when he first woke up.
I know where he went.
[OBI] There's no doubt
they entered the forest.
Probably staying away from the
main paths to avoid detection.
[OBI]
Hoof prints.
[SAKAKI] They even went so far
as to break into the castle.
We're most likely up against
a large organization,
Your Highnesses.
Do you have any idea
who it could be?
[SAKAKI]
One of the major possibilities
is a troublesome group that
has overrun the east sea.
The Claw of the Sea, correct?
Yes, exactly, Prince Raj.
Look at how well you're doing.
And you only studied
national affairs a few days.
[RAJ grunts] Are you being
sarcastic towards me?!
[KIKI]
The Claw of the Sea?
Prince Zen, I've actually
heard that name before.
You have?
They're buccaneers who illegally
collect tolls out at sea.
They use any means necessary
to avoid all inspections.
Money isn't their only priority.
They also trade in people
with particular abilities
or especially unique
appearances.
Those who tend to stand
out act as tools, or bait,
for the type of fishing they do.
Yeah, sounds terrible
and everything,
but Kazuki told me he wasn't
tracking Shirayuki down
for her red hair.
Not that we can
trust what he said.
At least we have a direction.
That's better than
searching randomly.
If you want to investigate
the Claw of the Sea,
I know where you
should go first.
The mountains. Correct?
Yes.
[RAJ]
Hmph!
The mountains?
[SERVANT A]
Excuse me.
Prince Raj, the king
has requested you
take Zen Wisteria to see him.
He said at once.
[ALL gasping]
To see my father?
Whoa. Requested by the king.
I never got to meet him
when I was a noble!
[ZEN] Here it comes. What will
the king do about Shirayuki?
Will he even do anything?
[SHILA groans]
You'll be fine, but your
ankle is definitely swollen.
When did this happen, again?
Oh, the last time I had night
watch, I sorta tripped.
[RYU] Chief, I've brought you
the reports on the new herbs
that we've been testing.
What perfect timing.
Ryu, would you make a poultice
for this brave soldier?
Sure. Since he's in pain,
I can add some alisia herb.
Please do.
[KAI]
...as it happened, stupid.
That was the day Prince Zen
left for Tanbarun, wasn't it?
Although, I guess it was
in the middle of the night.
You were probably half-asleep.
No, I wasn't!
D'you say Prince Zen
went to Tanbarun?
[SHILA]
Mm, yes.
He left in the middle of
the night with no warning.
But, Shirayuki's there,
so he probably just wanted
to be with her. I think it's
so sweet that they decided
to go on holiday together.
Yeah.
Did the prince happen
to say anything
about Shirayuki before he left?
[SHILA]
No, not in particular.
Right?
[KAI] Right. He was
in a hurry, though.
Tanbarun? I've never been there.
We should take the day
off and go sometime!
[SHILA] All you ever think
about is having fun.
[ITOYA] How much longer will
the sleeping medication last?
Oh, I'm guessing about
a few more hours or so.
That sounds good.
We don't need her waking up
and making things
more difficult for us.
Why is this empty?
There's a spring not too
much farther ahead.
I'll get water. You should
rest here with her.
[KAZUKI]
I will, thanks.
[exhales] We can
finally go home.
You just have to wait
a little longer.
I'm taking you to where
you truly belong.
Pops is gonna be so happy.
Hm? Already? That
wasn't very far--
[gasps] Why are you here?
Prince Zen Wisteria
of Clarines.
This situation we're in.
It's rather shameful.
I give my consent for you
and your attendants
to move freely in my kingdom.
That being said, keep in mind.
You may not conduct yourself as
if you are in your own kingdom.
However, you may act
with Raj's authority.
[ZEN] He's helping me on the
condition that I be discerning.
I'll take it.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
[ZEN]
I appreciate your consideration.
Our goal here is to rescue
the girl, Shirayuki.
I don't plan on
revealing my title.
At least not until I have
the villains on their knees.
I bet it's going
well in there. Yeah.
[ZEN]
Thanks for waiting!
Zen!
[KIKI]
How was it?
Good.
The king gave his permission
for us to do what we need.
We can move freely now,
so let's start the search.
[KIKI]
That's great.
[MITSUHIDE]
We need to investigate fast.
Mihaya. Looks like you get
to come along with us again.
Well, what a surprise.
I guess it's nice to be needed,
even if I am resented.
[RAJ]
Zen.
I, uh, I would also
like to accompany you!
Are you sure?
[RAJ]
I made a promise to her.
To Shirayuki.
We'll see. Next time.
When I come back to visit again,
I can't wait to hear all of the
townspeople talking about
their prince with pride in their
voices. I know that they will!
As prince, it is shameful
for me to simply stay here.
I think I can do more than
just pray for her safety.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Now, let's go bring
Shirayuki back together!
I welcome your help.
[TANBARUN KING]
How about that.
I never would have guessed my
idiot son would be out there
and not hiding away
in his room right now.
Interesting fact,
he finds it important
for Shirayuki and Prince Zen
to take him seriously.
Ah. When I found out
she was coming,
I assumed it was on a whim,
but that does not
appear to be the case.
And now another prince
is here for her.
You'd almost think
this Shirayuki girl
specialized in bettering
immature royalty.
She must be brought
back safely. Understood?
[SAKAKI]
Sire.
[ITOYA gasping]
[ITOYA]
Kazuki?!
Kazuki!
Damn it.
[gasps]
[OBI grunts]
[ITOYA groaning]
So, how's your neck doing?
You get to tell me where
Shirayuki is, now.
What?
Are you saying you're not
the one who just took them?
They both are gone.
Her and Kazuki.
[ITOYA]
It's a claw!
Let go of me.
We have to go help them.
[OBI]
What do you mean?
I don't have time to explain!
If I don't tell my crew
now, it'll be too late.
Please!
If this is an act,
it's pretty convincing.
[OBI] But I will not let you go.
You're taking me with you.
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Where am I? What happened?
It's that boy!
[KAZUKI grunting]
[KAZUKI]
Ow!
[KAZUKI groaning]
[KAZUKI]
Why are you here, too?!
No. Oh. God, no.
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
Quickly! Cover up your face!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ah!
What the--? Umihebi?
Good. So you're awake.
What are you trying to do?!
Where the hell are we?!
[UMIHEBI]
Oh, don't be so dramatic.
You were hiding from us.
What were we supposed to do?
Not come get you?
Who's that?
I told you. I'm not a part
of your crew anymore!
You're adorable, but
that's not up to you.
Be grateful you got
to stretch your wings
and have sweet dreams.
And don't worry,
we have plenty of work
for you to do now.
Yoo, hoo? Girl with hair
as red as the rose.
You understand the
situation, my pet.
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen's watch.
That's right!
It fell off at the castle!
Let her go! She has nothing
to do with you people!
You have no reason to keep her!
We've been following
you for a while,
so we know that we have
every reason to keep her.
Oh, those mountain men.
It'll be fun to find out
how much they want her.
You should know.
After all, you're friends
with them, aren't you?
If we play our cards right,
that exhausting old man might
even shut his trap for good.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What are they talking about?
You should tread more
carefully, pirate.
Remember on land,
you're nothing.
Uh!
The fairest face.
Oh, how I wish you wouldn't
make me hit it so often.
[SHIRAYUKI whimpers]
I'm so sorry, but you won't be
able to go back home anymore.
[SHIRAYUKI whimpers]
[UMIHEBI laughs]
[KAZUKI]
Stop! Don't touch her!
[UMIHEBI] Well, you kids should
at least try to get along.
Oh, make sure you don't touch
anything above the neck.
Please, what's going
on? I'm so confused.
[KAZUKI] After we took
you out of the castle,
you and I were attacked by one
of those evil woman's companions
when we were by ourselves.
[inaudible]
When I came to, we were
in here together.
So in other words,
you're saying,
I was kidnapped
from my kidnappers?
Basically, yes.
[gasps]
Listen, I'm not quite
sure where we are yet,
but these people are the
pirates that are known
for ruling the sea.
No matter what, we can't
let them get us on a ship.
If we don't get away fast,
no one will hear from us again.
[UMIHEBI]
I'm so sorry,
but you won't be able
to go back home anymore.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen.
[MUKAZE]
And prepare the ship!
[ZEN]
You dragged her out by force.
[SHIRAYUKI]
You're going to kill him!
Please, stop!
[MUKAZE] We don't abide
by the rule of kings.
That's why our people trust us.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I haven't heard Zen's voice
in what seems like an eternity.