[IZANA] If that's the case,
then you should make me an ally
on the path you and
Shirayuki have chosen.
[ZEN]
I need her by my side.
She's the only one
I want to be with.
When you're getting
the dust out, be gentle.
And it's heavy, so
take care with it.
Right.
[coughing]
Ah... Ah...
Ah-choo!
[gasps]
[ZEN]
Uh?
Shirayuki. Good morning.
Hi, Mitsuhide.
Good morning to you, too!
[MITSUHIDE]
Listen, Shirayuki.
Have you noticed that Zen's
been acting weird lately?
Huh?
He just seems a bit
distracted and distant.
It's so unlike him.
[MAID A]
Shirayuki!
[SHIRAYUKI, OBI]
Hm?
[MITSUHIDE]
Mm?
[MAID A panting]
Did something happen?
[MAID A] I'm terribly sorry,
but you're needed at once.
Prince Zen has been
injured quite badly.
[MITSUHIDE, SHIRAYUKI]
What?!
[SHIRAYUKI] So then the
tapestry fell on top of you
from upstairs and
hurt your neck?
Yeah.
Is there pain when
you turn your head?
There is.
[BOTH] We're... We're incredibly
sorry, Your Highness!
[ZEN]
It's all right.
I should have been paying
more attention, anyway.
Just try to be more careful.
[MAIDS]
Yes, Your Highness.
[ZEN]
You may return to work.
[MAIDS]
Thank you for understanding!
I can't believe they were crying
when you were the one hurt.
I was distracted instead
of being more alert.
I can't blame them for that.
Are you sure you're all right?
I mean, are you absolutely
certain this isn't serious?
Yes, I'm fine.
Oh, I am so sad it hurts
to turn my head right now.
[MITSUHIDE] There you go
with that attitude again.
[sighs] Shirayuki, can we talk?
I'll go let the chief herbalist
know what happened to him.
In the meantime,
will you look after Zen?
Oh, sure!
He'll listen to you.
That I'm sure of.
His words might seem spiteful,
but I think he just wants
you to stop worrying.
Yes, you're right.
[knocking]
[MITSUHIDE]
Pardon me.
Huh?
Excuse me. Chief,
are you in here?
[glass shatters]
Uh? Well, that's just great.
[MITSUHIDE] This has an
interesting fragrance.
I wonder what it is.
[MITSUHIDE gasping]
[MITSUHIDE] I can't make
Zen wait in pain like this.
[OBI]
What's taking Mitsuhide so long?
Should I go find out
what happened?
I was enjoying the peace and
quiet, but I guess you should.
Oh, look, here he is!
[OBI]
Mm?
[MITSUHIDE]
Prince Zen!
I sincerely apologize
for my tardy return.
I've come back now, and
I'm here at your service.
[ALL]
Hm?
The chief herbalist requests
you let her examine your injury.
I must accompany you to the
medical wing now, Prince Zen.
Why in the world are
you talking like that?
Um, Mitsuhide.
Did something happen to you?
[MITSUHIDE]
Shirayuki.
Were you concerned that
I was away so long?
You're so lovely.
I hate to make you worry.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ah...
Who is this guy again?
[GARAK]
It looks as though Mitsuhide
accidentally inhaled
the fumes of a medicine
made from a flower with
hypnotic properties.
[ZEN]
He's hypnotized?
Do you mean he thinks
he's someone else?
Not at all. Actually,
it's the opposite.
To put it in simple terms,
parts of his subconscious that
usually lie buried are free now.
He's just expressing them
without any inhibitions.
All that said, he doesn't
seem to be injured.
Tell me something, Mitsuhide.
You smelled an odd fragrance
coming from the medicine.
Did you happen to entertain
any intense thoughts
at the moment you inhaled it?
I did, as a matter of fact.
I was thinking about
how Prince Zen
has had a lot on his mind
and seemed distracted of late.
I felt guilty. I thought if
I had remained by his side,
this might not have happened.
What does that mean--? [groans]
Prince Zen. Is there
anything I can do?
I'm fine, would you
just back off?!
[GARAK]
That makes sense.
I believe the potion's
hypnotic effect has manifested
primarily by deepening
your loyalty to Prince Zen.
We prepared that stuff
for you, Shirayuki.
I had intended for hypnosis to
be one of the primary subjects
of inquiry on your
upcoming exam.
I'm having an exam?
I'm sorry about all
of the trouble.
But can you help him?
Get rid of his symptoms?
[GARAK]
We can make an antidote,
but it will take some
time to prepare.
[MITSUHIDE] Prince Zen,
please don't ask that of them.
I cannot bear for my failure
to create more work
for anyone else.
From what I understand,
the symptoms will be
gone in a few days.
It should cause me no pain.
[ZEN]
What?
[MITSUHIDE] Rather than concern
yourself with my medical issues,
you should really focus
on your own recovery.
[ZEN grunts]
I would argue
that you're actually the
one who needs serious help!
That may be.
However, I'm not sure
I understand my problem.
And even if your injury
isn't serious,
if you avoid using your neck
like this, it could get worse.
You must treat it now.
If you insist on following
me like a shadow,
you're going to make
me injure it further.
I'll break it while trying
to get away from you!
[MITSUHIDE]
Shirayuki,
will you treat Prince Zen
as soon as possible?
Uh, yes!
[ZEN]
Mitsuhide!
[exhales] I give up.
Go do whatever you want.
But, Zen.
[ZEN] You don't have to
treat him, either, Chief.
If you say so, Your Highness.
Now, Shirayuki. Please treat
the prince, as instructed.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, right.
This way, Zen. Follow me.
I'm counting on you, Shirayuki.
This is great.
[KIKI sighs]
[ZEN] Sorry for taking you away
from your work, Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
You're not. This is my work.
Oh.
I'll need to put this
on your neck.
You're going to have to
remove all your shirts.
Uh?! All of them?
[SHIRAYUKI] If it would hurt,
I can do it for you.
No, it's okay!
I'll do it.
Right, here goes.
Okay.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, Zen?
Let me know if you want
something from behind you.
Behind me?
Yes.
I know it hurts your
neck to turn around.
So if you need anything
from back there,
you just let me know.
[ZEN]
Thank you.
Hey, Master--
What's going on?!
Why are you naked?!
It's still light outside!
She's putting ointment on m--!
Ah!
[gasps] Found it!
Yoikagari, a plant with
hypnotic properties!
[OBI]
Really?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yeah. An unusual plant.
It's not a species we grow
in the castle's herb garden.
I was wondering why you had that
stack of books on your desk.
You were trying to find it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I had to!
I knew I wouldn't be
able to sleep tonight
unless I solved this.
But I still need to talk to
the chief herbalist about it.
Shirayuki.
Ryu?
[RYU] The chief wanted
me to give this to you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, wow.
Yoikagari!
[RYU] That's right. She said
you needed to study it,
since the prince wants an
antidote for his attendant.
And by the way, with that,
you've got your work cut out.
I'm going to try and sleep.
Right!
[SOLDIER A] Miss Kiki,
good morning to you.
Good morning.
Excuse me, Prince Zen.
[MITSUHIDE]
Excuse me, Prince Zen!
Uh!
Oh, Kiki. I'm so
incredibly sorry.
Did I cause any injury to
your lovely, glorious hand?
Good morning.
[KIKI]
Uh.
Morning.
[yelps]
[OBI laughing]
[ZEN] He's not back to normal
after a good night's sleep?
Then I guess his condition
is more serious than mine.
[MITSUHIDE]
By that implication,
can I assume you mean
your tragic injury
has finally healed?
Yeah, too bad yours hasn't.
Please do not concern
yourself with me.
These are the reports from the
areas under your jurisdiction.
Will you please look
over them now?
I'd like your feedback
by the end of the day.
[ZEN grunting]
He's the epitome of a young,
noble upstart to a tee.
[HARUKA]
I understand, Your Highness.
I will make the
arrangements at once.
I'm counting on you.
On to the next issue--
Prince Zen.
It's time for your
next appointment.
[ZEN sighs] I'm not done
with this conversation!
Time is of the essence,
Your Highness.
If you're late for this meeting
it will make you tardy
for the next one.
That will cause a chain
reaction, which will carry over.
Your lateness could bleed
into subsequent days,
for who knows how long?
This trend might continue
to get out of hand.
It could cause a horrible
situation for all of us,
but if you leave now,
that will all be prevented!
[HARUKA]
Uh?!
[MITSUHIDE]
Please wait, Prince Zen!
[ZEN]
Uh...?
[MITSUHIDE]
You mustn't take this path!
We will find a detour!
I cannot allow you
to dirty your feet!
[ZEN groans]
This is dumb.
It is my duty.
I am sworn to protect you, no
matter how benign the situation.
[MITSUHIDE gasping]
[ZEN] Sorry, Mitsuhide.
Would you hand that to me?
[MITSUHIDE]
Yes, sir.
[ZEN grunts]
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh?! Please come back here!
Prince Zen!
[ZEN sighs]
I'm free from my captor at last!
[yelps]
I've been waiting right here
for you, your highness.
[ZEN]
It won't wear off!
Are you doing all
right there, Master?
[ZEN] I don't know, Obi.
It's just like the old days.
When Mitsuhide followed
me everywhere.
I felt so stifled, you know?
But now, I take our
dynamic for granted.
He's there, but he
gives me space.
When he gets weird like this,
it really messes with me.
So that must be why you
two fight all the time.
Obi. Stay in here
with me for a while.
[OBI gasping]
Whatever you say, Master.
Well, why don't I
sing you a lullaby?
I've been told I have
a beautiful voice.
[ZEN]
Never mind, get out.
[ZEN] Mitsuhide. Send
messengers to the areas
with issues in yesterday's
reports, two are marked urgent.
Who goes is up to you.
Right. I'll do it at
once, Your Highness.
Mm?
Prince Zen, are you
feeling fatigued?
No, not really.
Mitsuhide.
Sir?
[ZEN] What do you see
when you look at me?
I'd say you looked fatigued.
[ZEN]
Not like that.
I'm asking on a deeper level.
On a deeper level? Well, then.
I adore you.
[ZEN gasping]
[KIKI] Shall I make a
record of that statement?
No, of course not!
[MITSUHIDE]
Is something wrong?
Don't worry about it.
[RYU]
Mm?
Shirayuki. That girl
never stops.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Hm... So the medicine
is extracted from the
blue flower petals, then?
But it doesn't
have blue petals,
and none that I tested
produced any real reaction.
[SHIRAYUKI] I hope Mitsuhide
and Zen are getting along.
I hate it when they
fight too much.
[gasps] Is tonight
the full moon?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Now that I think about it,
I've read that the moon
can affect some plants.
Maybe that's it.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ah! Zen!
Hi.
I'm sorry if I made you jump.
I went to see you, and Ryu
told me you were here.
Incredible. Are all these
books about medicine?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yeah, for the most part.
[ZEN] That's amazing.
I just wanted to see you.
But by all means keep
doing what you were.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen?
[ZEN]
Mm-hm?
[SHIRAYUKI]
The other day,
why did you tell Mitsuhide
to do whatever he wanted?
Oh, that.
Because he was treating me
like I was on a pedestal.
Most of the time people act
a certain way towards me.
They acquiesce
because I'm royalty.
I'm always
hyper-aware of that.
But I know that some
people treat me well
for reasons beyond
my royal status.
[ZEN] Mitsuhide and the others
who serve me just treat me
like a person, and I love
and respect them for that.
Yesterday, he was
acting like someone
who doesn't see
me as a person.
Plus, my pride got
the better of me.
[SHIRAYUKI] Sometimes when
you're around Mistuhide,
you turn into a child
again, don't you?
What?!
You should put your friendship
before your pride.
As prince and attendant,
for sure. But beyond that...
Mitsuhide is important to you.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
What happened?
I think maybe the
ladder fell over.
[exhales] You all right--?
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI whimpers]
Zen!
Keep your head down!
Are you okay? Zen, Shirayuki?
That was impressive.
You didn't get hurt, did you?
Both of you are well?
Yes.
He seemed normal
for a second, huh?
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thank you for shielding us.
I'm glad you were here.
[ZEN] What about you.
How's your back?
Fine.
Why were you here?
[MITSUHIDE]
I couldn't find you anywhere,
and this is the last
place I looked.
I was worried about you because
I knew you've been tired.
I see.
Shirayuki.
Uh...
It's just like you said before.
I have to forget my pride.
I want you to heal Mitsuhide.
Then, I will do everything
in my power, Zen.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[BOTH]
Uh?
[ZEN]
What is it, Shirayuki?
[SHIRAYUKI] I thought I would
try exposing it to the moon.
The properties of some
plants change when
they're under its light, so
I figured it was worth a try.
I didn't know this was one
of them, but I'm so glad!
I can make the
antidote from this!
And then, Mitsuhide can go
back to his normal self!
Master.
[KIKI]
Where's Mitsuhide?
[ZEN]
I left him with Shirayuki.
She's finally found
a way to cure him.
[KIKI] So you decided
to stop being stubborn?
[ZEN] I realized my pride
was just getting in the way.
We're friends, after all.
That's why we always stick
by you, Zen. No matter what.
It's the truth, and it looks
like Shirayuki abides
by the same code as us,
through thick and thin.
[KIKI]
Your Highness.
You still have a lot
to learn, don't you?
Ha, ha!
I do.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mitsuhide!
The chief herbalist is
finished checking my work.
The antidote's ready for you.
It's going to make you sleepy,
but I'll check on your
progress through the night.
When you wake up tomorrow,
you'll be back to normal.
I hope so.
[MITSUHIDE] I know I've annoyed
Zen these past few days,
and I've been kind of at a loss.
It's been difficult
for me to navigate.
I can imagine.
[gasps]
[MITSUHIDE]
Your hands are so pretty.
Ah! Really?
Oh, sorry. I didn't mean
anything weird by that.
When I heard that Prince Zen
had offered you his hand,
and that you'd taken it,
I realized that meant he
had finally found someone
that he could trust.
I can't tell you
how happy I was.
I'm grateful.
So you should know, I will
always be your ally.
The path ahead...
It will be difficult because of
the fact that Zen is a prince.
Shirayuki, I want you to
be sure of your decision.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[yawns]
Color has meaning.
And red is supposed
to represent fate.
My fate. Is this it?
[GARAK] Shirayuki is a really
hard worker, isn't she?
I can't believe she finished
the antidote so quickly.
[RYU]
Mm. She's quite dependable.
Looks like we finally found
someone you can trust.
[RYU]
Uh!
[ZEN]
What?! He doesn't remember?
Yeah, he's back to normal.
But he says the days he
was hypnotized are a blur.
So, uh.
It sounds like I caused quite
a bit of trouble around here.
Dare I ask what I did?
[ZEN growls]
[MITSUHIDE] I'm sorry
for whatever it was! Uh.
How's your neck, by the way?
It healed a long time ago!
[OBI]
Oh, don't you worry, Master.
I had a feeling
this might happen.
So I took it upon
myself to write down
pretty much everything he
said for the past few days.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh.
Here's an example:
when you bumped into Miss Kiki
while entering Zen's office,
you gently took her hand
and gazed lovingly into
her eyes and said,
"Kiki. Did I cause any injury
to your lovely, glorious hand?
Good morning. You look more
beautiful than ever today."
[MITSUHIDE gasping]
Wait, what?!
Is that true, Kiki?!
Why the hell do you look
so indifferent about it?!
Oh, this one's my favorite.
[MITSUHIDE] No, that's enough,
Obi! Hand it over!
[OBI]
Chapter one...
I'm glad it worked.
Shirayuki, thanks for this.
Sure!
Good, it looks like you're back
to your normal self again.
How are you feeling?
Fine. Thanks to
Shirayuki's genius.
Well, little genius. Are you
finished with your report?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh. I am! I have it right here!
Huh.
Good, this is excellent.
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes?
You just passed!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?!
Now, with this report approved,
I announce the completion of
Shirayuki's apprenticeship!
From this day forward,
she is hereby known as an
official court herbalist!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[ZEN gasps]
Wow! Thank you, Chief!
[laughs]
Congratulations,
you've earned it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thanks so much, Kiki!
Uh! Ryu!
Uh, I'm happy for you.
Thanks!
Honestly.
I had no idea you were
still an apprentice at all.
It just seems kind
of weird, doesn't it?
You've been around a while.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yeah, I guess so.
When I really stop to think of
my time here in those terms,
it has been a while since I came
to the castle and met you all.
Shirayuki. This is great.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen.
You predicted it that day.
There was something
that you wanted to do.
And you did it on your own,
just like you said.
You made your own
wish come true.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[MITSUHIDE] Shirayuki, I want
you to be sure of your decision.
Really consider it.
And decide if the place
where Zen will take you...
...is also a place
where you wish to be.
[IZANA]
How would you like things to be
between you and Zen?
[OBI] I've never seen
that expression before.
[RAJ] I feel like my current
relationship with you isn't bad.
[OBI]
That's my job.
Wait here, Miss.