[LADY A] It appears
Prince Raj and Shirayuki
will be spending the
whole day together.
And I heard it's to
deepen their friendship.
[LADY B] Sakaki was happy
about it, to say the least.
According to him, Prince Raj's
change for the better
didn't happen until after he
became friends with Shirayuki.
[LADY A] I caught a glimpse
of her when she arrived
at the castle earlier,
and what they say is true.
Her hair really is
as red as an apple!
So, someone managed to
change our big brother.
And how nice that
it was a woman, too!
--[RONA laughs]
--[LADY A gasps]
[LADY A]
Your Highness, wait!
[RONA]
Eugena, let's go!
What?! Go where exactly, Rona?
Haven't you been listening?
We have to investigate her!
Then, we can see for ourselves
what that Shirayuki is like!
Come on, don't you
wanna check this out?
[knocking]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh?
[OBI]
Miss!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Come in!
[OBI]
Interesting. Connecting rooms.
Well, that's convenient.
Let me know if you need
anything. I'm right there.
And I'm here!
[laughs] Understood.
Now, just to be sure.
You're not pushing yourself.
With Prince Raj, I mean.
Not at all.
Remember, I'm the one
who made this choice.
Great. Shall we go, then?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm-hm.
[SHIRAYUKI] Um, this tea
is extremely delicious.
Don't you agree?
[RAJ]
Yes. Of course it's good.
This particular blend is made
from the finest of tea leaves
to suit my elevated palate.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh. How wonderful.
[RAJ]
Hm...
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
Don't you find the flowers
in here beautiful?
[RAJ] No, they're a
little plain today.
This grand room needs much more
extravagant bouquets, obviously.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes, of course, yes.
[RAJ]
Mm...
[SHIRAYUKI]
So, I um, uh, Prince Raj?
[RAJ]
Yes, what is it?
[SHIRAYUKI]
I think I'm going
to head outside for
a bit to get some air.
[RAJ]
That's fine with me.
[door closes]
[RAJ sighs]
How do you think it's
going? Good or no?
I don't know why
you're asking me.
Yes, I do think it's so.
We might as well try, right?
I'm confounded by this.
What can that girl gain
by spending time with me?
What is she thinking?
If you asked me,
I'd say Shirayuki is trying to
meet you halfway, Your Highness.
In addition, perhaps you should
just focus on having fun.
I would if I knew
what to talk about!
What more can you
expect me to do?!
Just to figure it out for
yourself, Your Highness.
Ah...
It's a tough battle
in there, isn't it?
Very much so.
[SHIRAYUKI]
This view takes me back.
[OBI] I'd like to go
down there to the town.
Check out the bars and such.
[SHIRAYUKI] My home used to
be a bar. Did you know that?
[OBI]
Uh. For real?
[SHIRAYUKI] Yep, for real.
My late grandparents ran it.
I just thought they must have
been pharmacists or something.
I started raising medicinal
herbs while I lived there.
Speaking of your childhood.
Didn't you tell me you were
born in the mountains?
Yes. I lived there as a baby,
so I don't really remember
too much about it.
My grandparents took me
in fairly early on.
Oh, I didn't realize that.
I would like to see the
people who looked after me,
but I think I need to focus
on what I can accomplish here.
True. And great attitude.
This may seem a nuisance now,
but you never know if it will
lead to something good.
I actually learned
that from Zen.
Well, the next time
you come to this kingdom,
I'm pretty sure
you'll be able to go
wherever you want to go.
Yeah!
[RAJ]
Eh, Shirayuki.
[clear throat]
Since you traveled all this way,
I thought I could show
you around the castle
instead of just one room.
You'll escort me?
All right, thank you!
[KIKI] We've increased
the number of soldiers
and are continuing
the investigation.
However, we still haven't
received any helpful information
regarding Kazuki.
[ZEN]
I wish we could at least
figure out why this kid
is after Shirayuki.
What's the news with Mihaya?
He's in town at the moment.
I sent him to help the
soldiers investigate.
Meanwhile in Tanbarun,
Shirayuki's doing what
she can to help us out.
So let's do what we can
here to help her out.
[BOTH]
Mm.
[RAJ]
Inside Schenazade Castle,
we have many walls
decorated with amber,
many halls decorated
with wind chimes,
and a greenhouse featuring
some of the rarest
plants in the world.
What would you like to see?
I think the greenhouse
sounds nice.
The greenhouse?
Very well.
[OBI]
Excuse me.
Going there should be fine,
but you may wanna know you're
being watched from the shadows.
I'm what?!
[SERVANTS gasp]
[GUARDS gasp]
Now that you mention it,
there do seem to be more
soldiers than usual.
This is not a play!
[growls]
[gasping]
If you'll follow me.
Uh? Yes, of course.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What is this?
[RAJ] The entrance to the
underground passages.
They're not used a lot,
but we can get to the greenhouse
without being watched this way.
I bet it's easy to
get lost in here.
[RAJ] They were made to be used
in case of an emergency.
It can certainly be
difficult for someone
who isn't familiar
with the passages.
[gasps] Do you think it will
be safe for us, Prince Raj?
How rude!
I've been here enough times to
know exactly where we're going!
I apologize. No offense
was intended.
[RAJ grunts]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Is that the way?
No, it's still farther up ahead.
[RAJ]
Mm...
So, uh, how much longer do
you think this will take?
We'll be there soon!
Just be quiet and follow me!
All right, but didn't we
walk down this path earlier?
[RAJ gasps]
Your Highness, we're
not lost, are we?
We're not! I know where we are!
The exit is...
Right this way!
Why is this a dead end, now?!
Yes, why, indeed.
You know, we're kind of
wondering the same thing.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Well, maybe it's not a dead end
and there's a way
to open the gate.
[RAJ]
Oh! Look up there!
If we pull those chains
at the same time,
we should be able to raise it.
[OBI]
If you say so.
I guess I'll take
the one on this side.
Ready when you are.
[OBI]
I'm ready.
[RAJ]
Three.
Two.
One!
[OBI gasps]
The wall!
[RAJ]
Huh?
[OBI]
Look out!
[SHIRAYUKI]
What? It's an arrow.
Your Highness, are you hurt?
No, I don't think so.
[gasps] I just remembered!
There are traps all
over the place down here
in case we have
invaders or pursuers.
[SHIRAYUKI] Then, I think it
would be best to turn back.
[RAJ]
Oh, great. How inconvenient.
Huh?!
[gasping]
[RAJ whimpers]
[OBI] So, looks like we'll
just keep moving forward.
What in the world
is going on here?!
Again, we're kind of
wondering the same thing.
Well, this is hardly my fault.
I'm not the one who put
the traps everywhere.
[SHIRAYUKI] No one's
blaming you, Prince Raj.
Why don't we stay put and
wait for help? All right?
[OBI]
Hm...
[RAJ]
I should probably mention that
no one comes down here.
Not unless there's
some emergency
or during patrol in the morning.
We're on our own until tomorrow.
[OBI]
We've walked a long way today.
[SHIRAYUKI]
True.
I hate it here. [groaning]
[SHIRAYUKI] Oh, are you
all right, Your Highness?
[RAJ] Without a carriage, I
cannot continue any farther!
Go on, don't worry about me!
[SHIRAYUKI]
We can't.
We'll be completely lost
without you, Prince Raj.
[OBI] Our lives are also at
stake in case you forgot.
I just can't believe
this happened.
You know, it's starting to feel
like being together is bad luck.
I'm sure you agree, Shirayuki.
No, our relationship
is a different issue.
Prince Raj, let's go!
We can rely on your memory!
[gasps]
You... can rely?
Let's get out of here!
You don't have to tell me that!
[EUGENA]
I think we should go back.
[RONA] No, this is our chance
to see how things are going.
Besides, did you see how she
motivated our brother just now?
That was amazing.
What if all those rumors are
true, and she really is special?
Shirayuki.
Where's Zen?
Outside.
He had an appointment with
the bird handler squad.
He knows Shirayuki is working
hard, so he's working hard, too.
I see.
I came to get his signature,
but I might as well
see how it's going.
[ZEN]
Excellent, as usual.
It's been a while since I heard
the sound of that whistle.
Hello, Kihal.
[KIHAL] Hello. It's good to
see you again, Your Highness.
Um. Do you know if Shirayuki's
working, right now?
Yes, She's actually away
from the castle on business.
Uh? That's a surprise.
You had a souvenir
for her. Didn't you?
[ZEN]
Souvenir?
Yes. To thank her
for helping me.
I made her a bell accessory out
of walnut stone from the island.
Walnut stone, huh? I can
give it to her for you.
Please! Thank you,
Prince Zen.
I'm sure she'll love it.
Regarding the bird
handler squad. Tell me,
would it be better to have
soldiers go to the island,
after all, to simplify things?
[KIHAL] Yes. I think
it'd be easier to start
with the same type of training
that we do on the island.
[gasps]
[ZEN] Very well. I will
make the arrangements.
[KIHAL]
And we will do everything we can
to prepare to receive them.
Thank you. I don't
doubt you will.
[MITSUHIDE]
Prince Izana.
I'm just seeing how
things are going.
Looks like he's doing
his job well.
He is.
What is it?
I wanted to ask you
something, Your Highness.
Are you testing them?
Is this all just a test for
Prince Zen and Shirayuki?
[IZANA]
Hm.
It is.
[MITSUHIDE]
Mm!
Oh, come on, now, why do
you look so surprised?
[MITSUHIDE] I... didn't
expect you to answer me.
Why?
It's not something I have
need to hide from you.
If those kids give this up,
I suppose I will just file it
away as a rather boring story.
Prince Zen has become stronger.
That's Shirayuki's influence.
And I believe he's made
her stronger as well.
I do wonder what the
future holds for them.
For now, it will be interesting
to watch their next move.
[MITSUHIDE gasps]
Mitsuhide, come over here.
[MITSUHIDE]
Yes, Your Highness.
[MITSUHIDE gasping]
Whoops, looks like they
found out about our rendezvous.
Prince Izana!
[IZANA]
Go to your master, Mitsuhide.
[MITSUHIDE sighs]
[MITSUHIDE] That side of
him is exactly like Zen.
Are you all right?
He's heavy.
Surely, there's something around
here that will make the water
recede or create some
sort of path for us.
[SHIRAYUKI]
No. It's probably best
if we get through without
touching anything.
[RAJ groans]
[SHIRAYUKI grunts]
[RAJ]
Good work there, Obi.
[OBI]
Yeah, thanks.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi?
Sorry, Miss,
do you think you could
wait here for just a minute?
Wait, it's too dangerous!
Nah, I'll be right back.
What do you think he's
going back that way for?
Hope he'll be all right.
Uh?
[OBI]
There's a path now.
I must've scared them
away from crossing it.
[OBI grunts]
I think maybe that
was excessive.
Not even close, he's fine!
But, might as well
see for ourselves!
[EUGENA]
Uh! Rona, wait!
[RONA] He probably can't move
and is trying to keep quiet.
[OBI] What a surprise.
I didn't expect children.
[RAJ]
Did you just hear that?
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'll go take a look. Stay here.
[RAJ] Hold on! Can't you
just leave it to Obi?
What if something happened
to him, and he needs my help?
[RAJ]
And what if that happens to you?
This is about more
than just you!
What do you think Prince Zen
would say if you got hurt?!
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Prince Raj.
[RAJ]
Yes? What is it?
[SHIRAYUKI] If you believe
my words and actions
are some sort of threat,
then I will return to
Clarines immediately.
Your Highness,
it wouldn't benefit either
one of us if I were to stay.
All right, not what I meant,
but now I wonder why you came.
Was this all just
for appearances?
Get here, say you couldn't bear
it, and go back home to Zen?
Are you stupid?!
I'm here because I wanted to
try and be friends with you!
[RAJ gasps]
The truth is...
...whenever I meet people,
I try to form a connection with
them in whatever way I can.
And I always learn so much,
whether here or in Clarines.
I don't want to allow our
connection to go to waste,
Prince Raj.
No, we may not have met under
the best circumstances,
but I believe we can
change all that!
[RONA growls]
Let go!
[OBI] Well, I finally
caught the culprits.
Let go of me,
you insolent man!
What do you two think
you're doing?!
Lord Brother!
[gasps]
[EUGENA, RONA gasping]
Greetings. I'm Princess
Rona of Tanbarun.
This is my twin,
yet younger, brother.
I'm Second Prince, Eugena.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, wow, a princess!
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintances.
My name is Shirayuki.
[RONA]
I know. I've heard about you.
Anyway, have you been
following us down here?
Princess Rona, Prince Eugena,
do either one of you know
the way to the exit?
We don't.
We lost our way as
we came in, as well.
I know how to get out.
Which exit would you prefer?
Why did you admit that?!
I wanted to watch them
a little longer!
But I want to
go outside, Rona!
Stop fighting!
Just show us the way!
[RONA, EUGENA]
Hmph!
[SHIRAYUKI laughs]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh?
[RAJ sighs]
[RAJ] We took an unexpected
detour, didn't we?
Yes, but still, some
good came from it.
[RAJ]
Huh?
It was the first time you've
ever looked in my eyes
when you were speaking to me.
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
There are so many rare flowers!
And you have medicinal
herbs, too.
Go on, look around.
Take your time.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I will, thanks.
[RONA]
Hello, Brother.
[RAJ gasping]
We have been watching you
while you watch Shirayuki.
Tell the truth.
Are you in love with her?
[gasping] Why would
you even say that?!
Are you trying to scare me?!
Of course not. I heard
Sakaki talk about it.
[SAKAKI]
What's the matter, Prince Raj?
It's hardly like you
to think so much.
[RAJ] Right. I just cannot
find the answer.
[SAKAKI]
Answer?
[RAJ]
Yes. In the future.
As a prince, if there
is something I lack,
I'd like you to
inform me about it.
--[crash]
--[gasp]
[SERVANT A whimpers]
You dropped that.
All right, but after you
saw Shirayuki in Clarines,
it seems like you've been
trying to reexamine yourself
and all that.
[EUGENA]
Mm-mm!
Oh, you're exaggerating.
I'm not "reexamining."
I am only trying to make
myself even more perfect.
Heh. Besides, I don't
know how long Shirayuki
is even going to
be at the castle.
She may get sick of me
and go home early.
Oh, Raj...
[footsteps]
[OBI]
Mm?
Obi, May I have a moment?
[OBI]
Your Highness?
I'm sorry there was trouble.
Can you convey that
to Shirayuki, as well?
Yes, Your Highness, of course.
What? Did you hear that?
He said that awfully
quiet, though.
[RONA] For our brother to
apologize for his own mistakes.
This is a huge step for him!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thank you so much
for showing me the
greenhouse today.
[RAJ]
You're welcome.
And please, feel
free to go back
as much as you want when
you have the time.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, Prince Raj?
I'll, um, I'll see you tomorrow!
Indeed.
[ZEN]
Mitsuhide.
Yes?
Earlier, why were you
with my brother?
[gasps] Oh, yeah, we were just
talking, that's all it was.
Ohh?
Uh... What are you oh-ing for?
I have no idea what my
brother might be thinking,
but we're not giving up.
Whatever he's doing
cannot get between us.
Yeah, that's what I told him.
[KIKI]
Zen.
[BOTH gasp]
We received a report that the
boy, Kazuki, has been sighted.
[ZEN gasps]
He has?
[KIKI]
Mm-hm. But, unfortunately,
Mihaya has disappeared from
the grounds of the castle.
[BOTH gasp]
[MIHAYA] I've been looking
for you, pretty boy.
[KAZUKI]
Oh, we've met before.
What is it? You have
business with me?
[MIHAYA] Well, I thought
I could make some cash
at the castle after meeting you,
but it wasn't going as expected.
So, I think I'll capture
the villain that's after Red
and just be rewarded for that!
To be honest,
it's a better plan!
Uh!
[MIHAYA yelps]
If you ask me, though.
You and I should work together.
Of course, I'll make sure that
you're paid very handsomely.
Who's paying? You?
The real "villain"
you mentioned.
My comrades will pay you.
[MIHAYA]
So what are you talkin' about?
Taking Red somewhere
more suitable
for her than the castle?
[KAZUKI]
Exactly.
[MIHAYA chuckles]
You're dreaming.
First of all, Red's
not even that cute.
Second, she has a terrifying
knight protecting her.
Isn't that standard
practice, though?
Kidnapping a princess
guarded by a knight?
[SAKAKI] There's a mysterious
charisma about that girl.
[RAJ]
I'm curious.
[SAKAKI]
Why don't you persuade Shirayuki
to stay in Tanbarun isntead?
[OBI]
I was thinking the same thing.
[RAJ] How would you classify
our relationship as it stands?