Could this be a nymph?
Um, hi.
[gasps, growls]
Who might you be?
What makes you think you can set
foot upon this sacred land
where all women are
forbidden to tread?
[NANAMI]
Women are forbidden?
Maybe that's why
he looks so angry.
I'm so sorry! I had no idea
I wasn't allowed here.
I'll just get out
of your hair now!
--[JIRO] Stop!
--[NANAMI yelps]
Are you the one who made
these cherry blossoms bloom?
What is your name,
and why have you come here?
[cries]
Answer my questions, woman!
Your response shall determine
if I break your arm.
Master Jiro!
[NANAMI gasps]
Wait, Jiro?
That means this guy is the
creep who hurt Botanmaru!
[MAMORU chirps]
[JIRO grunts]
[NANAMI pants]
[JIRO winces]
Stop.
[COMMON TENGU]
There you are, Master Jiro.
I was looking for you.
You are needed back at the hall,
sir. Is something the matter?
I'm merely surprised that a
woman's arm can be so frail.
[NANAMI panting]
What's his problem?
That guy's got
serious anger issues.
But do you really think
that Brother Jiro
becoming the fourth successor
will make everything
better on the mountain?
[NANAMI] There's no way that
jerk could fix anything!
[TOMOE] I was beginning to
worry you had fallen in.
So does "go to the bathroom"
actually mean waste your time?
Tomoe!
[NANAMI cries]
What is wrong?
Why are you trembling?
Tell me what happened.
[NANAMI]
Trembling? I am?
No wonder. I feel like
I'm about to collapse.
You encountered Jiro?
Are you all right?
Poor thing, I hope
he did not hurt you.
[NANAMI] Uh, actually,
I'm the one who met him.
I'm okay, but he did
threaten to break my arm.
I wish I had known
women weren't allowed
on this mountain, though.
I probably wouldn't have gone
walking all over
the place like that.
What a relief nothing
important happened!
[TOMOE slurps]
[NANAMI
'Nothing important"?
I must say, I had heard
tales of his violence;
however, I never really expected
Jiro to be such a brute.
Raising a fist in anger has
always been his first response.
Truly, I should
have known better.
I shall make it up to you by
having a new bathroom prepared.
Uh! Stop acting like
I'm not here! Look at me!
[NANAMI gasps]
[SUIRO gasps]
I beg of you, please
do not resent me.
I have lived with this
mountain's customs a long time.
Thus, I am not comfortable
interacting with women.
Especially when faced
with a beautiful maiden,
such as yourself.
[NANAMI]
Why do I get the feeling
pretty boy doesn't mean
that as a compliment?
So that's why you didn't
let me use your bathroom?
No, it is because the toilet
here lacks plumbing,
and a woman's "business"
should be like her cheeks,
always flushed.
[KURAMA]
Great dinner topic.
On the subject of
doing our "business",
there's something
we need to discuss.
Something that's left over.
Oh? But it would appear
you cleaned your dish,
including the
pickled vegetables.
I am glad to see that your
tastes have finally matured.
How could he not? These
pickled veggies are delish!
I didn't mean leftovers
literally, guys.
I'm talking about my father's
sickness here; we need to focus.
These are Peach Pills.
Nanami got this miracle cure-all
straight from the Medicine God
when she was in Izumo.
They're our best bet
for curing the old man.
Have him throw back a few of
these bad boys and we're set.
Once he's in full health,
the mountain should go back
to the way it was, too.
And Jiro's succession will
have come to screeching halt.
If they are what you claim,
I do not doubt their potency.
Even against an illness
as grave as the Sojobo's.
Be that as it may,
administering this medicine
to him would be impossible.
[SUIRO] The Sojobo collapsed
about two months ago.
Since then, he has
been hidden away
in some sanctum
on the compound.
Brother Jiro maintains
all official duties
as Master of the Hall, including
keeping security tight.
No outsiders are
permitted within.
And due to my banishment,
that includes me as well.
Entrusting the medicine to
an insider is an option,
but even then it is unlikely
to reach its intended mark.
Jiro would be quick to
stop such an operation.
[JIRO grunts]
[NANAMI]
He would do something like that.
[KURAMA grunts]
[SUIRO] But you should not
brood about this too much.
These things always have a way
of working themselves out.
Why not enjoy some fresh apples?
[KURAMA] What, you're just fine
with things staying like this?!
Don't worry about Brother Jiro;
I'll handle him.
He's not going to stop me
from seeing my father!
That is far too dangerous.
I cannot allow you
to risk your own safety.
Can't allow me?
I'm not a little kid anymore.
The only reason I came here
is because I thought there'd
be something I could do
other than running away.
I'm not who I used to be.
[NANAMI]
Kurama.
No. This is still
beyond your ability.
Uh! But why?
[INSTRUCTOR]
Shinjuro!
[ALL]
Huh?!
I'm so glad you
finally came home!
And you're all
grown up now, too!
Uh... Who are you?
It's me!
[KURAMA]
Oh.
I'm sorry, Shinjuro! When
I told him you were back,
he just couldn't
wait to see you!
[GREAT BROTHERS]
Shinjuro! Shinjuro!
[INSTRUCTOR] Shinjuro has
at last returned to succeed
his father as the fourth Sojobo!
What a wonderful day!
Uh. Hold on.
I think you've got
the wrong idea.
[INSTRUCTOR] The Sojobo
is an elderly man.
[GREAT BROTHER A] Even if
he pulls through today,
who knows what
tomorrow shall bring?
[GREAT BROTHER B]
Finding a suitable successor
is of the utmost importance!
[KURAMA]
Uh! Uh...
Shinjuro, this is for
the sake of the mountain.
Surely, you would not
abandon us again.
--[GREAT BROTHERS talking]
--[KURAMA] Uh? Succeed?
--But I don't want to.
[KURAMA gasps]
[GREAT BROTHER B]
Yes, you must have!
[INSTRUCTOR] Shinjuro, you are
the only one who can rightfully
fill the void that will be left
in your father's passing!
[clap, clap]
[SUIRO] That is quite enough
for today, great brothers.
Shinjuro has just returned
home after being away,
and he is tired. Let us discuss
these intricate matters later.
--[INSTRUCTOR] Right.
--[GREAT BROTHER B] Mm.
[GREAT BROTHER A]
Yes, of course.
[SUIRO]
'Tis alright.
You should not let their
words weigh on your mind.
[SUIRO gasps]
Where are you going?
[KURAMA]
Please excuse me, everyone.
I think I need a moment
to clear my head.
Do you think Kurama
will be okay?
[TOMOE] Hard to say, it seems
he has no desire to be the heir.
Not surprising. After seventeen
years in the mundane world,
why would he
wish to return?
Lady land god, I ask you,
if I deliver the peach
pills to the Sojobo,
would you please do
me a favor in return?
Take Shinjuro and descend the
mountain tomorrow morning.
You need not become
involved in our affairs.
Too bad, because we're
already involved.
We're here to support Ku-, to
support Shinjuro however we can.
So we're not leaving until
he says so. Understand?
[SUIRO chuckles]
When I reunited with
Shinjuro at the main gate,
imagine my surprise to see
that he brought a woman.
I realized then, he is no
longer the child I once knew.
He has grown so much while
away from this mountain.
And has surely left
behind an entire life
in the mundane world.
One that he cannot abandon.
That is why expecting
him to become
part of the mountain
is not fair.
Tell me, lady land god.
Do you truly know Shinjuro?
[NANAMI gasps]
[SUIRO] He has always
faced his challenges alone.
Even if they overwhelm him,
he will recklessly push himself,
for he could never exploit
another's kindness.
I have known Shinjuro ever
since he was a small child,
and yet, he has never
come to me for help once.
But I did what I could.
I continued to watch
over him in hopes
that he would let me shoulder
his heaviest burdens for him.
Please, take him home.
Before he takes on the burden of
becoming the fourth successor.
[TOMOE]
You could never pull it off.
Uh?!
If you are incapable of
determining someone is behind
you prior to them outright
breaking silence,
then you stand no chance of
sneaking into that compound.
It's funny you say that,
I was actually thinking
the same thing.
Even from all the way out here,
the great hall feels
domineering.
They've doubled their
triple layer barriers;
talk about overkill.
Let me guess, Suiro wants
you to take me home, right?
[TOMOE]
Yes.
I tried to talk a big game,
but when ya get down to it,
I don't have a clue
what I'm doing here.
And Suiro completely
called my bluff.
I feel so humiliated
I could die.
[TOMOE] What do you want
to do? This is your call.
[NANAMI panting]
Kurama!
[KURAMA yelps]
Well? C'mon, what's our plan?
[KURAMA]
Uh?
I wanna sneak into
that compound,
and give my old man
the medicine personally.
Would you maybe
help me do that?
[wind howls]
Huh? What did you say?
I couldn't hear you because
the wind was so loud.
One more time?
What? Uh, nothing!
I didn't say anything!
[NANAMI]
Hey Tomoe, you heard him right?
What did he say?
[TOMOE]
He asked for our help.
Of all the stupid questions!
Of course we'll help you!
[FUMIMARU]
Brother! Please!
Just one more chance!
I am sorry, Fumimaru.
As decreed by Master Jiro,
we cannot accommodate feeble
tengu at the hall any longer.
[FUMIMARU whimpers]
[BROTHER TENGU] Whether your
future is in the woods
or down the mountain
is for you to decide.
[door slams]
[CHIYOMARU] First, Brother Usa,
and now Brother Fumi.
He was so kind, too. [sniffles]
Don't cry, Chiyomaru.
You won't be far behind him
if they catch you like this;
then what'll you do?
Although, it probably
doesn't matter,
we'll all get kicked
out eventually.
I wish things would go
back to the way they were
before The Third got sick.
Don't say that! I'm gonna get
banished, I just know it!
[DAIDAIMARU]
It'll be okay, brothers.
[CHIYOMARU, TAKEMARU]
Hm?
The Third will get better
again in no time.
That's what our celestial nymph
sister said; so it'll be okay.
[DAIDAIMARU]
Our sister!
She made the eternal
cherry blossom tree bloom!
So pretty and warm.
Just thinking about her
makes me start to smile.
And then I don't
feel sad anymore.
I feel warm instead!
[YATORI]
Hello, Master Jiro.
I heard you had another tengu
kid leave the nest today.
The way they're flying the coup,
there won't be anybody left.
So be it. Those who
are weak of spirit,
or lack strength, are not
welcome in my compound.
I must make sure only the
strongest shall live here.
Though what concerns me more
is your presence here tonight.
How did you get
past my barriers?
[YATORI] Oh, yeah, there
were barriers, weren't there?
Thing is, they're full of holes.
I must admit, I expected better.
A barrier's only as strong as
the heart and mind of its maker.
Perhaps your heart and mind
are in disarray, Master Jiro.
[JIRO grunts]
Whoa! Now that's more like it!
There's no way I could
get around this one!
[YATORI groans]
You dare imply my heart
and mind bear weakness?
[YATORI muffled]
That's crazy! I'd never do that!
No, you would not!
Be gone.
My spirit is as strong as steel.
I will never waver
in my convictions.
Curse that woman.
This was her doing.
[JIRO]
I have to know who she is.
You must be joking.
Hey, I'm not stoked
about sharing
a room with you either, okay?
Suiro knows you're my familiar,
and he's trying to
be accommodating.
And why are you
being such a baby?
It could be worse.
I can't even change
my clothes in here.
So it's really not that
bad for you, is it?
[bed squeaks]
Good grief. That certainly
was a close one.
[NANAMI]
Oh, yeah,
because you're totally
the one in danger here!
Speaking of, I'm
wearing lots of layers
so you can't jump
me like last time!
Good plan. Barring the fact
that when you are asleep,
your shirt often lifts up
and exposes your torso.
[NANAMI gasps] You were takin'
in the sights, weren't you?
Peeping has never
been my intention.
In truth, keeping you where
I can watch over you
is all I have ever cared about.
Huh?
You may rest easily.
For even if your clothes
come clean off,
my heart and mind shall
remain entirely pure.
[NANAMI] You're such a big,
stupid jerk! Ah!
[KURAMA]
You guys still awake?
Brother Suiro gave me a
map of the whole compound.
Tomorrow is the day
we're sneaking in.
What?
[KURAMA] A powerful barrier
surrounds the facility.
We don't stand a chance
of getting past it,
unless we're invited
in as guests.
There are probably a few more
barriers we'll have to find
our way around once we
get inside the place, too.
As Master of the Hall,
Jiro is in charge of defense.
That won't be a problem, though,
'cause we're gonna
divide and conquer.
Here's how it goes.
Team one gets Jiro
drunk with this liquor.
Meanwhile, team two
goes to find my father.
Would it not be easier for us
to dispose of Jiro altogether?
Maybe, but I don't
want anybody
inside the compound
getting hurt.
The real question is, how
do we get them to welcome
us past the first barrier
and not arouse suspicion?
Uh. Pardon.
Master Shinjuro?
What the-? Why are
you still here, Botanmaru?
I am sorry to interrupt you,
but please let me help!
I wish to heal the Sojobo!
[NANAMI]
Botanmaru.
No way. You need to stay
here with Brother Suiro.
If something goes
wrong out there,
I won't be able to save you.
Hold on a sec. If we're
splitting into two groups,
it'd be better for us
to have more people.
So, we need to decide on
who's dealing with Jiro,
and who's searching
for the old man.
Of course. Being that
I am her familiar,
I shall go with Nanami
and search the compound
for the Sojobo, which
leaves you free to handle
the Jiro problem
all by yourself.
Wait, what?
That's one plan.
But why don't we explore some of
our other options first, okay?
Jiro would recognize Nanami,
she cannot make the attempt.
Master Shinjuro! I would
gladly accompany you, sir!
I already told you no!
[BOTANMARU whines]
[NANAMI]
Hang in there, Botanmaru!
[KURAMA]
You stupid fox!
[TOMOE] Dealing with a tengu
should be a tengu's job!
Consider Nanami's foolishness.
She is entirely incapable
without me by her side.
[NANAMI] Shut up!
I'm a strong, independent woman,
and I don't need you
watching over me!
[NANAMI]
How 'bout this.
I will go look for
Mister Sojobo,
and I'll take Botanmaru with me.
And then the two of you can
keep Jiro distracted, okay?
You've gotta be joking!
I'm not!
Don't worry!
I just had a brilliant idea!
It's a sure fire plan to get
us invited past the barrier!
--[TOMOE, KURAMA] Uh...
--[NANAMI giggles]
[TOMOE] Nanami's foolishness
knows no bounds.
This plan of hers
is absolutely absurd.
I should have known
she was up to something.
She never says
anything intelligent
when that grin is on her face.
[TOMOE]
And so it begins.
[NANAMI grunts]
[TOMOE]
Such a pill of a girl.
What is it about her
that captivates me?
[NANAMI]
Potty.
[TOMOE]
Uh!
[NANAMI]
Gotta. Potty.
[NANAMI groans]
[TOMOE]
That girl, I swear.
And after all of the trembling
she did earlier.
I can go with Botanmaru to
search for Mister Sojobo,
but the rest is up to you!
You'd better not try to take
advantage of me tonight
while I'm trying to
get my beauty sleep!
Oh, please.
[TOMOE]
Damn.
Why will she not just accept
my protection of her?
How does she not realize?
I am unable to do anything else.
[TOMOE gasps]
Hey! Your futon is
on the other side!
[TOMOE] Keeping you where
I can watch over you
is all I have ever cared about.
[TOMOE gasps]
[NANAMI gasps]
[TOMOE]
So you may rest easily.
For my heart and mind.
Were supposed to remain
entirely pure.
Uh, Tomoe. What are
you doing in my futon?
[TOMOE]
I am not.
Your futon is over there.
Huh?! Oh, sorry about that!
[gasps] That was way
too close for comfort!
[NANAMI groans]
[NANAMI] Then again, why
do I have this feeling,
like he was holding
me tight in his arms?
Was I dreaming?
Or was it...
[KURAMA] I had no idea
you were so negligent.
It's your duty as my familiar
to help me get ready,
and yet you're only just
now crawling out of bed.
Look at you! Totally godlike,
but still a bad boy at heart!
[KURAMA]
Well, of course!
After seventeen years,
a runaway tengu,
having become a land god,
finally returns home;
a story like that requires
production value if we want
anyone to believe it.
Even the surrogate
leader Jiro can't ignore
an exiled brother tengu who
has ascended to godhood.
He'll have no choice
but to welcome us
as supremely honored guests!
Onwards! To the
Kurama main hall!
But before we go,
I think a test of my newfound
land god powers is in order.
What do you think, fox?
If you do not value your life,
then by all means,
give them a try.
By my word, I order you
to act like a cat,
spin around in place,
and give a hearty "meow!"
Meow!
[gasps]
Holy crap!
This talisman is awesome!
I have complete control
of Sacred Word Binding!
Kurama! Keep that talisman
hidden in your clothes.
Now both of you quit
fooling around,
it's time to get serious.
[TOMOE] It appears you
need to "get serious."
What the hell are you wearing?
This is my disguise!
Jeez, I have to at least try
and not look like a girl.
[TOMOE]
I hate this plan.
Because of you, I must be
subjected to the tengu's wrath.
Hey, while we have
a moment alone.
About yesterday...
It was dark,
and I was half asleep,
so I know I could be wrong,
but were you holding me in
your arms while I was sleeping
next to you last night?
Just wondering, I know you
said you don't think of me...
No, sorry. I was also
half asleep at the time.
I mistook yours for the warmth
of my friend Tanuko.
I was having a pleasant dream
of spending an evening
with her at the tea house.
However, as soon
as I touched you,
I realized you were not the lady
of my desire, and I awoke.
I apologize for my inappropriate
actions last night.
It was purely by accident.
Can you forgive me? Please?
[NANAMI]
Mm-hm.
[TOMOE]
Great.
Ugh.
Well that was awkward.
Do you need to
take a cold shower?
Or are you ready to go?
[COMMON TENGU B]
Brother!
A party claiming to be
Shinjuro has come calling.
[BROTHER TENGU B]
"Shinjuro," you say?
We are not expecting such a
guest. Do not open the gate.
Turn them away!
If you think we should.
--[blast]
--[gasps]
I appreciate the welcome,
common tengu.
I am Shinjuro, the eldest
son of Sojobo the Third.
As land god of
the Mikage Shrine,
I have come to witness the
fourth's rite of succession.
Now, where may I find Jiro?
[COMMON TENGUS murmur]
[TOMOE] What is the matter,
lowly tengus?
My lord and master
has a short temper.
If you do not wish to
be reduced to ashes,
along with your
hall, get moving.
[JIRO] It appears Suiro's
letter was in good faith.
If a god has come calling,
then we have no choice
but to welcome him.
Please make your way inside.
[NANAMI] All right!
So far, so good.
This is our chance
to find the Sojobo.
You can lead the way, Botanmaru!
[BOTANMARU]
Ah...
[NANAMI]
Come on, let's go!
[NANAMI] Layers of barriers are
woven all across this compound.
And somewhere within
this maze is The Third.
We have to find him!
[NARRATOR]
Kurama and Tomoe have managed
to infiltrate the front gate!
Let the drinks flow,
and the good times roll!
Oh, wait, they get caught.
Meanwhile, Nanami and
Botanmaru find the Sojobo!
But something's not quite right.
Next time,
"The God Is Blindsided."
They're so doomed!