[NARRATOR] In a way, I can turn
all Jiro's stuff into my stuff!
Get outta my way!
C'mon, step aside!
Ee!
What?
Now that's what I call
a barrier against evil!
[CHIYOMARU]
Oh wow. What's this light?
Are you okay?
You're not hurt are you?
[DAIDAIMARU]
Mm-hm. What's happening?
This weird light is making
me feel all safe and stuff.
It's like our nymph sister
is giving me a hug,
and keeping me warm.
I must find Nanami.
Now that she has
been successful,
I am certain she
is looking for me.
Nah. She is too busy trying
to find the Sojobo's soul
after taking down Jiro's
barrier to bother with you.
She also said for me
to give you this,
and you would know
what to do with it.
Clever girl, a land
god's white talisman.
I hid it deep within
this compound.
No one can find it if I'm gone.
Best of luck ever
solving that mystery,
and bringing him
back to the living!
[NANAMI] Where the heck could he
have possibly hidden a soul?
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI]
Crap, a dead end.
Why would it lead me here?
[NANAMI gasps]
Move.
[NANAMI]
A door?
[JIRO]
One that leads underground
and has been sealed
for many years.
This is the only place
on the compound we tengu
would never tread. To think
that bastard knew about it.
[NANAMI]
Wait! I'm coming, with you.
[NANAMI] If I were smart, I'd
wait for Tomoe and the others,
but I'm not about to let
Jiro go in there alone!
[MAMORU squeaks]
[meeps]
This path goes awfully
far underground.
Why did it get sealed off?
[JIRO]
There was an accident.
A tengu was
permanently disabled.
Approximately
seventeen years ago.
Within this cavern dwells Mount
Kurama's Thunderbolt beast.
You would be wise
to fear its wrath.
[NANAMI] Um. When you
say disabled, you mean?
He shall never again take to
the skies. Just as he deserves.
[SUIRO sobs]
[JIRO] You should have
left that brat alone.
Those tears are wasted, Suiro.
[JIRO]
He learned firsthand,
making friends is just
another weakness.
[NANAMI] The Thunderbolt
beast is at the bottom?
[NANAMI gasps]
Great, the Sojobo's soul
is down there, too.
[JIRO]
Stay here.
Don't move. No matter what.
[MAMORU chirping]
I know. I don't like this
anymore than you do.
[NANAMI] He's acting so
differently than before.
It's like he's given
up his fight.
The whole time we've
been down here,
he hasn't looked at me once.
[NANAMI, MAMORU shriek]
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI]
That thunderbolt was intense!
Lightning like that wouldn't
need to strike twice!
[MAMORU chirps]
A tengu was
permanently disabled.
'Kay.
[NANAMI]
I'm going, too.
--[JIRO] Suiro.
--[SUIRO weeps]
[JIRO]
Such foolishness.
It was not worth
the cost of your wings.
Those tears are wasted.
[SUIRO cries]
I cannot help it.
This pain, but when
I thought about how
Shinjuro may have
died down there...
[growling]
The thunderbolt beast.
It appears my scent
has caught its attention.
Well then.
[NANAMI screams]
[JIRO]
Huh?!
Oh no!
--[MAMORU squeaks]
--Uh. Y'know,
I really wasn't expecting to
find this thing so quickly.
[roars]
Mamoru! Barrier against evil!
[SUIRO] When I thought
Shinjuro may have died,
I couldn't stop myself.
I had already taken action.
[SUIRO] To save someone
I love. I have no regrets.
This white talisman of yours had
better prove its worth, tengu.
Chill out. This'll lead
us to the sojobo's soul,
and Nanami shouldn't
be hard to find from there.
[KURAMA gasps]
Hey, wait a second!
Not that way.
[KURAMA]
Why this place?
I can't go back down
there! Not again!
Master Shinjuro,
what is the matter?
[KURAMA]
Wait. I'm not a kid anymore.
All we gotta do is get
the soul and find Nanami.
Then, I can go back
home where it's safe.
[JIRO groans]
Jiro! You protected me.
But why?
[JIRO] Get away from me.
I'm a fool now, too.
Like him, I'm weak,
all because of you.
[THUNDERBOLT BEAST roars]
[NANAMI]
Ah!
[NANAMI sighs]
[TOMOE]
When put up against my fox fire,
I would hardly call you
"thunderbolt beast."
Perhaps "kitten" is more apt.
Tomoe.
[THUNDERBOLT BEAST roars]
Letting your curiosity
get the best of you?
As they say, that will cost you!
Are you all right, Nanami?
[NANAMI]
Jiro! Hang on!
[TOMOE]
Uh!
[NANAMI] What should I do?
He's hurt really bad.
This is all my fault.
I'm so sorry. [cries]
[JIRO]
Don't cry.
I brought this on myself.
Seeing the woman I love,
die before my eyes,
was more than I could bear.
[TOMOE]
What?
[KURAMA]
Love?
[NANAMI]
Huh?
[THUNDERBOLT BEAST gags]
[THUNDERBOLT BEAST gagging]
Ew, gross!
What the hell did that
thing just throw up?
[NANAMI] Look! It's all
shiny and glowy and stuff!
[KURAMA]
I don't care! It's still gross!
His soul.
It must be the Sojobo's
missing soul.
[NANAMI gasps]
I see.
He hid it within the stomach
of the thunderbolt beast.
That explains everything.
Shinjuro, you must
return it to the Sojobo.
It's up to you now.
What? But I'm an outsider.
No. You are the only
one who can do it.
I no longer have the right
to stay here on the mountain.
Nor do I possess the dignity
to look the Third in the eye.
It falls to you.
I cannot trust anyone else.
Please.
[KURAMA]
Mm.
Jiro! Jiro!
[JIRO]
Do not cry.
I want my last memory
to be of your smile.
If I could see it one more time,
I would take it with me,
and hold it forever as
I walk alone in darkness.
[COMMON TENGU A] Ah!
Master Jiro's been hurt?
[COMMON TENGU B]
What are we going to do now?
[NANAMI sobs]
[TOMOE exhales]
[TOMOE] How long are you
going to weep like that?
I can't stop,
it's all my fault.
Do not let this affect you so.
We administered the Peach Pills
promptly, thus he shall not die.
Give him two or three days,
and he will be well again.
But what if Jiro
can't fly anymore?
How would I ever
be able to apologize
for something like that?
You would not.
Even if such a burden
were to befall him,
Jiro would happily bear it
knowing that he saved you.
[SUIRO] Why hello, Master
Familiar, and also Lady Nanami.
Oh! Mister Suiro!
I received word that Jiro
had been badly injured.
I came to see if there is
anything I could do for him.
You should not
look so displeased.
I'm sure he will be all right.
But first, have you
seen Shinjuro?
Yeah, he's with
the Sojobo right now.
Just wait, it won't be much
longer until the Third wakes up
from being sick,
and he'll be good as new.
I'm sure everyone in
the village is excited.
The dark clouds are
gonna go away,
then new plants will grow,
and the mountain
will be beautiful again.
[KURAMA]
Why would I send him a feather?
I can't believe you fell
for such an obvious scam.
[KURAMA]
What's up with that, old man?
You getting slow?
Ah, well.
[NANAMI] Everything will heal
and come back to life.
[SOJOBO]
Hm.
[NANAMI]
And even the flowers
on the cherry blossom
tree will bloom.
[NANAMI]
Weird. By crushing these leaves
I can make a medicinal ointment?
Man, the tengus' book
on herbs is awesome.
[NANAMI] It's been two days
since the Sojobo woke up.
And bit by bit,
everything on Mount Kurama
has recovered as well.
Everything except Jiro.
Brother Jiro is
going to be fine.
According to Brother Suiro,
his body has been healing
exceptionally well.
Seriously, you should
not worry about him.
He will be okay.
You should be thinking about
going back home soon.
I get what you're saying,
but I just don't feel like I
can leave until he wakes up.
[BOTANMARU]
Mm.
Hey, uh.
Have you been back to the
eternal cherry blossom tree yet?
Its flowers have bloomed.
We should go see them!
[JIRO]
These dark clouds.
Why are they just lingering
over the mountain?
Damn it! The plants cannot
flourish in this condition.
[JIRO grunts]
[SOJOBO] Jiro. What is it
you are up to this time?
[JIRO]
Uh! Sojobo!
My deepest apologies, sir.
I take full responsibility for
the sorry state of our home.
A bad guy came,
and he confused me,
I could not tell what the
right thing was anymore.
I do not deserve
to stay on the mountain.
[SOJOBO]
Hogwash, my boy.
[JIRO]
Uh!
[SOJOBO]
Everyone makes mistakes,
you are too hard on yourself.
No one has ever been perfect,
nor can they ever be.
It is the one enduring truth
that ties us all together.
Shinjuro is no different.
Fumimaru and the
other young tengu
will blunder through
life as well.
Consider Suiro.
He may seem composed
and infallible, but he has
a nasty habit of knocking
over my poor bonsai trees.
Absentminded, though he may be,
the amazing thing about him
is that these little offenses
never ruffled his feathers.
And of course,
I make mistakes as well.
Every soul does
from time to time.
You are no worse
than anyone else.
[JIRO]
Thank you. Huh?
The clouds.
Those thick clouds
are clearing away!
At long last! I can see
the mountain again,
and that maiden.
I can see her as well.
[JIRO]
This light.
I would love to walk through
it with her by my side.
[NANAMI]
Huh?
[BOTANMARU, DAIDAIMARU giggle]
Hey, is something wrong?
No, I'm okay.
But, I think I just
sensed Jiro's presence.
Attention! Master Jiro
has finally woken up!
Brother Suiro is tending
to him as we speak!
[NANAMI gasps]
[BOTANMARU]
That's great!
[JIRO]
Peach Pills?
If not for that medicine,
you would have lost your life.
You must be grateful
to that young girl, right?
How does it feel waking up
to your shattered dreams?
That was quite harsh.
Perhaps, but while you were
laying down on the job,
Shinjuro kept the affairs of
the compound running smoothly.
The Great Brothers are
all very proud of him
for taking on your role.
In honor of your recovery,
tonight he is planning for his
last deed as acting leader
to be a cherry blossom
viewing party.
You will attend with me,
won't you?
I suppose.
[NANAMI] Mister Suiro!
I heard that Jiro's awake!
Oh, god!
Please excuse me!
[NANAMI]
It's been two days.
And all I'd thought about
was Jiro getting better.
His confession didn't
even cross my mind.
I can't believe I forgot.
He said he loved me.
Wow. After all that,
you could not even
speak to the poor guy.
I panicked! No guy's ever
said he loved me before!
I don't know what
I'm supposed to do!
You hurry up and thank him or
apologize, whichever you want.
[NANAMI]
Ahhh!
[TOMOE] After all,
we are leaving tonight.
[NANAMI]
Tonight?
[TOMOE]
Yes, is that a problem for you?
[NANAMI]
No, it just seems kinda sudden.
[TOMOE]
With Jiro finally well again,
surely there is no reason
for us to stay any longer.
[NANAMI]
He has a point.
I guess that's true.
Of course, if you do
not wish to go back,
you could always stay
here by yourself.
Yeah?
And what exactly am I supposed
to do if I'm all alone?
Obviously you could
spend your time
getting to know
Jiro better.
I always knew tengu
were tasteless.
But in your case, you should
consider yourself lucky
that any form of
beast would fall
for a scrawny little
girl like you.
Y'know, you're right.
He seems like a sincere guy that
would actually cherish me,
unlike a certain unappreciative
fox that I know.
Yes, he seems to be
of fine character.
Plus he would call you
adorable pet names,
such as "celestial nymph."
No one would blame you if
you chose to walk that path,
and I certainly
would not stop you.
Yo, let's go, you guys!
It's time for the cherry
blossom viewing!
Kurama!
[KURAMA] C'mon,
everybody's waiting for us!
Get a move on, fox; what are
you just lying around for?
[NANAMI]
You're awfully excited.
Duh! It's a celebration.
One last hurrah
for Jiro's health!
And then we can
finally go home.
[TENGUS chatter]
[SUIRO] Brother Jiro put in
the order for this meal
in anticipation of the Fourth's
succession ceremony.
Though that is cancelled,
we accepted delivery from
the caterer anyway.
I ask that you eat to your
hearts' content this evening.
A toast, in celebration
of Jiro's health
and the revival of the mountain!
[TENGUS] Cheers!
I am not feeling up to this.
Please excuse me.
[SUIRO]
Not so fast.
Do your duty as the guest
of honor and mingle.
[NANAMI]
Botanmaru!
[JIRO grunts]
[BOTANMARU]
Oh! You are here!
[NANAMI]
Wow! Everything looks great!
Yes, originally it was going
to be for Jiro's succession.
Please stop.
[SUIRO] You may take any open
seat that you would like.
Nanami, take this seat.
Sweet! Tri-color dumplings!
Maiden. You are welcome
to the seat next to me.
[NANAMI gasps]
Um. I wanted to thank you
for saving me from
the thunderbolt beast.
I should be thanking you.
The medicine you
brought along
kept me from suffering any
permanent repercussions.
Hey, am I crazy,
or are the other tengu
trying to get as far away
from us as they can?
They are.
None of them are accustomed
to being around women.
[NANAMI] Probably should have
thought more about that
before I agreed to come.
[JIRO]
Here.
[gasps]
Uh... uh!
[NANAMI screams]
[NANAMI] Oh man!
Way too high! Tomoe!
[JIRO]
Open your eyes. You are safe.
[NANAMI gasping]
Beautiful! It's like I'm
inside a flower!
Have you come to like
the village of Kurama?
I have! I can't believe
how clean the air is.
Not to mention, the kids
here are too freaking cute.
Well, you could stay,
if you'd like.
Master Familiar. You are
spilling sake everywhere.
Whoops. Let me get that.
Whoa! My apron's not a towel!
[TOMOE] I need a napkin.
[KURAMA] You are
hilariously pathetic, fox.
If you're that worried about
her, I could always take you
up there so you can
chaperone them.
[TOMOE]
Worried about her?
I have no idea what
you are talking about.
Stop! Knock it off!
So you're cool with those love
birds sitting in a tree?
They could be K-I-S-S-I-N-G.
He does not possess the
nerve to force himself
upon Nanami without her consent.
If she wanted me to
look after her,
Nanami would have
called for me by now.
As a human,
her life is short.
She should spend her time
doing what makes her happy.
If staying here with him
fulfills that criteria,
I will not stand in their way.
[KURAMA sighs]
As someone who's actually
spent time with humans,
let me give you some advice.
Human lives are short.
So if you have something you
want to say, then say it now.
Or before you know it, you'll
have missed your chance.
[JIRO] I wish...
I wish you would stay.
[JIRO]
It would be nice.
I forgot. I still have
to return your medicine.
[NANAMI]
Oh, thank you!
[JIRO] If not for those. I would
have likely lost my wings,
just as Brother Suiro had
when he met the beast.
Those pills are more
effective than I'd heard.
Is making this medicine one of
the traditions of your shrine?
Not exactly. I traded
some donuts for these.
[JIRO]
Donuts?
Yeah, ya' see, I originally
got them to help protect Tomoe.
Maybe someday,
if Tomoe ever decides
he doesn't need me anymore and
he wants to go off on his own,
I can give him these
as a parting gift.
He's strong,
so he never lets anyone help
him or watch his back.
[JIRO]
Uh.
[NANAMI] That's why. This is
the best I can do for him.
[JIRO]
I see.
I had no idea how precious
this medicine was.
Sorry you wasted some on me.
Oh. No, don't worry it's
not like that at all!
[JIRO]
A little while longer.
Do you mind if we stay like this
for just a little while longer?
[JIRO] I will burn this
image into my mind.
And when I close my eyes,
I will be able to see you again
sitting amongst the flowers.
--[SUIRO] My goodness!
--[NANAMI] Tomoe!
--I am terribly sorry!
--Tomoe! Tomoe!
[SUIRO] Lady Nanami had
gotten herself drunk
before I realized
what was happening.
--[TOMOE] What? How?
--[NANAMI giggles]
Why is this girl rolling
on the floor wasted?
[SUIRO] It would seem she
ignorantly overindulged
on sake-flavored buns.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe! [giggles]
I think we're done.
I wanna go home now.
Ah! Thanks a lot,
Mister Suiro!
[BOTANMARU]
You are okay! You will be fine!
It washes off, I promise!
[NANAMI] I can still hear the
music from that celebration.
I want to visit them again.
Maybe in the spring.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe! Come on, Tomoe!
Where the heck did Kurama go?
[TOMOE]
To hell, if we are lucky.
Hey, that tengu mountain
was a lot of fun!
Let's do it again! Tomoe,
are you listening to me?
I'm talking!
Oh, I hear you.
[sighs] I love you.
So much.
[NANAMI snores quietly]
[TOMOE]
I know.
I love you, too.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe's back felt so warm.
I was comfortable, too.
Being carried by him like
that made me so happy.
Well it's about damn time!
I've been waiting!
[NARRATOR] Kirihito
returns to the Netherworld
to retrieve Akura-Oh's body.
Nanami and crew pay
a visit to the Year
God's shrine for a new talisman.
They pass through the tori gate
said to review the
last twelve years,
but that twelve year
hangover is a drag.
Wait, where's Nanami?
Next time, "The God Goes
Back to Being a Child."