[NARRATOR]
My name's Botanmaru!
I am looking for an older tengu.
He is the son of Master
Sojobo the Third.
[gasps] Look! Up there!
We found him!
What? No, no, no, no, no, no!
Shadow Die.
What's up? Your call
was very unexpected.
Unfortunately, my evening
is already spoken for.
I didn't come here
for myself, Kurama.
I brought someone who
really wants to meet you.
Who?
[NANAMI]
Botanmaru.
[BOTANMARU]
Uh...
It really is you!
[gasps] Who the hell
is this brat?
Hello, my name is Botanmaru of
Mount Kurama, and, and you see,
I have been wanting to meet you
for so long and now, and well,
now that I have, I just...
I wanted... Mm...
[KURAMA]
Save it.
[BOTANMARU gasps]
[KURAMA]
I don't know what you want,
but you need to get back home
before they know you're gone.
[BOTANMARU, NANAMI gasp]
Descending from the mountain is
out of bounds to the Premature.
I bet you didn't tell anyone
where you were going, did you?
If you're a runaway and you're
looking for a babysitter,
then you definitely
got the wrong guy.
Get lost.
[NANAMI]
Hey!
That's not it.
I have come to bring you
back home, Master Shinjuro.
Right now, Mount Kurama is
in lots of big trouble.
Ever since Master
Sojobo collapsed,
the mountain has been
under a cloud of miasma.
They picked Master Jiro to
be the fourth successor,
but most everyone does not
want him to be in charge.
So every day up there, all we
do is wait for answers.
Master Shinjuro, we need
you to return to us.
What exactly do you want
me to do about it?
Come on, Botanmaru.
Here's the story, kid.
I got the hell outta that
place over seventeen years ago.
I'm just a failure.
The mundane world scene
is where I'm happier.
Besides that, so many girls
down here are smokin' hot.
No! Stop it!
You're not some failure,
Master Shinjuro!
You're actually my,
you are my role model!
It's because you
are just like me,
that is why you have to
be the one to fix it!
Botanmaru, what's the matter?
The poor little guy is too young
to have come to this world.
[BOTANMARU panting]
[KURAMA] Tengu children get
their strength
from Mount Kurama.
So we can't descend
into the mundane world
until we're adults.
The mountain can't
protect us here.
He's taken in too much
of this toxic air.
How'd he get those scars?
They're from the lashings.
Uh?
[KURAMA]
Oh, man.
Huh?
Well, this is unexpected.
I hadn't planned on going
back home so soon.
[BROTHER A]
What's up, Shinjuro?
Your wings still as
small as your brain?
[BROTHER B]
Can't stop riding crows?
I bet you suck your
thumb too, ya' big baby.
[BROTHER C] You might
be the Sojobo's son,
but you're still
a pathetic loser.
[KURAMA] The Sojobo's son was a
target for the elder brothers.
[INSTRUCTOR]
Shinjuro, please change.
Your dress is too informal
for the great worship.
I'm dressed fine as I am. I'll
wear what the rest of them wear.
Why would I put on clothes
of a higher rank?
I'm nothing but inferior
to everyone anyway.
That's why they all hate me.
[SHINJURO yelps]
[INSTRUCTOR]
You mock our tradition!
[KURAMA] All it felt
like to me was a burden.
[SHINJURO]
As of now I sleep here.
Brothers, I look forward to
making friends with all of you.
[BROTHERS chanting]
[KURAMA] I've never even
had an actual conversation
with my father. Only met
him a couple of times.
[SHINJURO]
He was shaggy.
Is that what I'm
going to look like?
[KURAMA] Looking back, I didn't
even realize how lonely I was.
Why is my bed missing?
[BROTHER A laughs] Oh, is
that what that nasty thing was?
Well, it reeked of old milk,
so we tossed it.
--[BROTHERS laugh]
--[SHINJURO] Jerks.
[SUIRO]
Hey, Shinjuro.
[SHINJURO]
Hm?
[SUIRO] You can sleep here with
me tonight if you would like.
[KURAMA]
Until I met Brother Suiro,
I had never known what
genuine kindness was.
[KURAMA]
Here's the deal.
I'm taking the kid back with me,
after that I'll go and find
out how The Sojobo's doing.
You can come with, but I'm
not promising excitement.
[NANAMI]
That's not what I want.
I showed up to support
you, Kurama!
I mean, you're gonna need all
the extra help you can get!
Well, check it out,
all these talismans will
definitely be a good start!
What a shocker to discover
that you are in fact the
true son of the Sojobo.
Your tengu performance was
so incredibly riveting.
Hey, what's with inviting the
emo fox boy? Why is he here?
I have a penchant for watching
melodrama as a leisure activity.
[KURAMA]
Is that so? Here's what I think.
You were afraid that I'd
be alone with Nanami,
and you clearly aren't
cool with that idea.
[TOMOE]
What?
You guys, can you quit
your stupid arguing
until we get there?
You'll wake up Botanmaru!
[BOTANMARU]
Mm. What happened?
Hey, welcome back!
You got exhausted and passed
out, but don't worry,
we gave you a peach
pill so you'll be okay.
Your arm's looking
a lot better, too!
They're gone! But how?
Peach Pills are the
gods' miracle cure.
A pure panacea that
remedies everything
from injuries to illnesses.
I do not have the faintest
notion of the malady
that befell the Sojobo,
but these may heal him.
Fox, is that true?
'Tis "Master Fox", you zygote.
You flew quite a
lengthy distance
for someone who doesn't
even have use of his wings.
[BOTANMARU] Well, I...
I rode a crow to get here.
I said I wanted to bring you
back but had no way to fly,
so Brother Suiro said he
would help and gave me one.
[NARRATOR] The mundane world's
Mount Kurama is like an echo,
a pale reflection of the
one the tengus live on.
[KURAMA] The secret entrance
is through Sojogadani.
Ah! The air's so clean out here!
This way, through the trees.
Once we pass this point,
we will be on Mount Kurama.
After we arrive,
you will fulfill your destiny.
[NANAMI]
You weren't kidding.
It's so dark here
I can hardly see.
You'd never know it was morning.
Fog is descending. You had
better stay close, Nanami.
The miasma here has
been known to cause
dimensions to contort.
If you lose your way,
you can never return.
This gloom is terrible.
Yeah. Since Master Sojobo's
presence has faded,
the evil spirits have gotten
stronger than ever.
I know when he gets better,
everything will probably
go back to normal.
But, someday,
in the very near future,
it is my hope the real fourth
successor will actually
turn out to be you,
Master Shinjuro!
[SHINJURO]
Brother Suiro!
[flute plays]
I want you to be the fourth
successor, Brother Suiro.
My dad is shaggy
and not very nice,
but you're beautiful and
kind enough to make even
the tengus of Atago
and Takao jealous!
Suiro, the fourth successor?
That is such a frivolous
notion, Shinjuro.
No, I really mean it!
You've got way faster
wings than anybody else,
and you play the flute
so wonderfully.
Will you please play it again?
My favorite song about
our cherry blossoms!
[SHINJURO]
Uh!
[SUIRO]
Wait just a moment.
This is appalling. Be honest,
has Jiro hurt you again?
It seems he's constantly
striking you behind my back.
I find that inexcusable.
Yeah? Well that's not the issue.
The real problem
is being a weakling.
Brother Jiro just, he doesn't
realize how strong he is.
Fine. I shall play it for you.
Your favorite song about our
beloved cherry blossoms.
--[flute plays]
--[KURAMA] Brother Suiro,
you were my favorite part
of life on the mountain.
This is all my fault.
[SHINJURO gasps]
[SHINJURO]
Brother Suiro!
[KURAMA gasps]
[BOTANMARU] Master Shinjuro?
What is the matter?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Hm? The fog looks even
thicker than before.
Are you alright, Nanami?
Hm?
Wait. Nanami and
Tomoe are gone.
[BOTANMARU]
Huh?
[KURAMA]
Oh, no.
It's the fog.
[BOTANMARU]
Where are you going?!
[KURAMA]
What is this anyway?
Some kind of a barrier?
Most likely an attempt to
prevent us from entering.
Well, I know I'm not
exactly welcome here,
but I still have to return
him to the village.
Botanmaru, we're turning back!
It's not safe here!
[gasps]
[SUIRO] You've grown up,
my dear Shinjuro.
And flying is now
second nature, I see.
One might almost think
you a respectable tengu.
Is-Is that you, brother?
Gaze upon the picture of
despair before you.
My wings are destroyed,
all because I foolishly
chose to help you.
[KURAMA gasps]
[JIRO]
Shinjuro!
You're twelve, you should
be flying by now,
but you're still weak! Let go
of Suiro's apron strings!
--[JIRO] Come on!
--[SHINJURO gasping]
--I'll retrain you!
--Stop it! You are hurting me.
[JIRO] If you don't use your
wings to fly out immediately,
the thunderbolt beasts
will savage you to death!
--Fly.
--[SHINJURO cries]
--Quickly!
--[SHINJURO screams]
But you were unable to fly.
I received word and
went to the cavern
of the thunderbolt beasts
to rescue you.
Then I was struck by lightning
and reduced to this ruin,
while you swiftly
fled the mountain
once your wounds had healed.
Please forgive me,
Brother Suiro. I only--
[SUIRO]
No need to apologize, Shinjuro.
You just have to die.
There's a fog in my heart.
Your death will dispel it.
I should have left you behind.
I should never have even
bothered with you.
I should have let you
die utterly alone.
Please don't say such
things, brother!
I don't have the
will to defy you.
I hated everything about
this mountain.
With one exception,
that was you, Suiro.
--[flute plays]
--[KURAMA gasps]
[KURAMA] It's the song of
our cherry blossoms!
[SUIRO laughs]
I know no such song!
[KURAMA] That's because you are
nothing more than an imposter!
[SUIRO groans]
I know, because I can
hear him. That's him.
He's at the top of the mountain
playing my favorite song for me.
I know the real Brother Suiro.
[flute plays]
Master Shinjuro!
Lookit! I found big time
lost Fox and the gang!
Hey that's insulting! You can't
just decide that we were lost.
[KURAMA]
Heh.
How am I going to face you?
[TOMOE]
My interest is minimal...
[KURAMA] Even though I still
harbored a lot of doubt,
I knew that I had to press on.
[NANAMI]
Shut up, Tomoe!
[KURAMA] This is it. The
tengu village of Kurama.
[NANAMI]
I know we just got here,
but I have to pee
so freakin' bad!
[MAMORU squeaks]
Why stand around yapping,
you guys?
Let's cut to the
chase and say hi!
[KURAMA] No. Wait, Nanami!
Please, I'm not ready!
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI]
He's so gorgeous!
Welcome home, Shinjuro.
--[BOTANMARU]  Hi, Brother!
--[SUIRO chuckles]
Thank goodness you've come
home safely, Botanmaru.
And you too, Shinjuro.
[SUIRO]
Mm?
[KURAMA] I'm sorry I haven't
stayed in touch, brother.
[NANAMI] I didn't think Kurama
would bow like that for anyone!
Please look up at me. I haven't
seen your face in so long.
[NANAMI]
'Scuse me.
Hi, I'm Nanami Momozono and
I'm serving as a land god.
That's Tomoe, my familiar.
We're real sorry for dropping
in on you like this
out of the blue.
The steep trail to
this height must have
wearied your companions. Please,
come with me back to my home.
[NANAMI]
What was that about?
[SUIRO] Our surroundings have
become very bleak indeed.
Because of this miasma,
new plants will not grow.
Even the eternal
cherry blossom tree
at the heart of our
mountain has wilted.
[NANAMI]
Gotta pee. Need a bathroom!
[KURAMA] But brother,
why are you living
in a dilapidated house so far
away from the compound?
I would've thought you'd have
a home on the temple grounds.
Well, it can be a little drafty
sometimes, but I do not mind.
I think you would be more
comfortable in the main hall,
but unfortunately, I do not
think Jiro would allow that.
[grunts] Brother,
it's all my fault
that you are no longer wanted
in the main hall, because I...
[NANAMI]
Um, Mister Suiro?
[NANAMI grunts]
[TOMOE] Master Suiro,
I do beg your pardon,
but nature is screaming
insistently
at my lady and mistress.
[NANAMI]
Ah!
Is that the case,
Master Familiar?
Then I shall direct you
towards the outhouse.
What with this house
being so shabby,
you'll have to
walk rather far.
[TOMOE] In that case,
I shall accompany her.
Uh, no thanks. You don't
have to come with me!
[NARRATOR] Here it is!
Everyone's favorite Main Hall.
[DAIDAIMARU]
Brother Chiyomaru!
A baby piglet boar!
Daidaimaru, you can't
bring such things here!
They'll punish you.
And the mother boar will
be looking for him.
[DAIDAIMARU]
But his poor mama was dead.
He was by himself,
standing by her body.
An evil spirit must
have gotten her!
If I had left him alone
he would be killed, too.
It's too sad!
Well, have it your way then,
but keep it a secret from
the elders, do you hear me?
[CHIYOMARU] They will
discard him if he's found.
[JIRO] If alone it would die,
then that was its fate.
Weakness must perish.
If you wish to live,
become stronger.
If your strength is not
enough to sustain you,
then it is your
true time to die.
[DAIDAIMARU grunts]
[YATORI]
Ooh, scary.
You are more intimidating
at this moment
than I have ever seen,
Master Jiro.
[JIRO]
Well, well, Yatori.
[YATORI] The eternal cherry
blossom tree, am I right?
Ever since that thing withered,
everyone on this craggy old
peak has lost their mojo.
Why not simply switcheroo with
a new tree, and be done with it!
If you get rid of that towering
tree all by yourself,
then everyone will
definitely sense
the advent of a brand new era!
What do you think?
Sound good to you?
--Manners, Yatori!
--[YATORI yelps]
Who smacks away like a common
farm animal before their master?
[YATORI whimpers]
[JIRO] The eternal cherry
blossom is our most sacred
tree of old! I will not
permit your foul mouth
to casually suggest
its elimination!
But, Master Shinjuro
has returned now!
You must find a new plan.
People are going to lobby
hard for him as the fourth, Sir.
And from the
looks of things,
you don't seem very popular.
So? I am by far the strongest
one in this place.
I do not care what
others may think,
I am most worthy to succeed.
I ran farther and flew
higher than anyone.
I trained day and night,
never idling a moment,
fortifying myself, all to
achieve maximum strength.
I must eclipse
the Third's powers
before he takes his last breath.
Only a few more days until
the rite of succession.
I will not allow a
single hindrance.
At last, it will not be
Suiro or Shinjuro, but me.
I will emerge victorious!
[NANAMI]
Man, you're killin' me.
There's no reason for a bathroom
to be farther away
than a bus stop.
And this is like four
bus stops away!
Mister Suiro didn't seem to
like me very much when we met.
Maybe he doesn't trust me.
You may not use my restroom!
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI]
This must be the village.
They're right, all the
trees are dead here.
It's because of
the cloud of miasma.
I wonder what kind this one is?
It's all rotten.
--[NANAMI yelps]
--[CHIYOMARU] Hands off, human!
What the hell!
Why'd you do that?
So cute!
Are you tengu kids
from around here?
[TAKEMARU]
Uh! It's heading this way!
[CHIYOMARU]
This is the mountain's
eternal cherry blossom tree!
Intruders who dare to touch
it suffer divine retribution!
An eternal tree?
So the story was true then.
But this tree looks all rotten!
[CHIYOMARU]
Stop! Leave it alone!
This is our sacred tree,
it's the heart of Kurama!
It only flowers
four times a year,
and its power and
beauty are unmatched!
[BROTHERS]
Ugh.
Brother, look at the chest,
it is swollen which can
only mean one thing!
[TAKEMARU]
A woman! We just met a woman!
Yeah? Is that a problem?
Uh-oh, we talked to her! The
elder brothers will freak out!
[TAKEMARU]
We're done for!
What's wrong with talking
to me? How insulting!
We are not allowed
to speak with women,
or even look them in the eye!
Especially young
beautiful women,
if you touch one they say you'll
fall to the mundane world!
Uh? Gee, that's awfully
sweet of you to say.
[TAKEMARU] What? Wait.
Is she beautiful?
Actually, Brother Suiro
is way prettier.
Okay, we're good then.
[NANAMI groans]
Will you please help me?
I need to dig a hole
at the eternal tree.
I want to give this wild
piglet boar a proper burial.
[NANAMI sighs]
[TAKEMARU] Ever since
Master Sojobo fell ill,
we've had a cloud of
miasma hanging over us.
Evil spirits are appearing
everywhere,
and the animals are dying off,
even the eternal cherry
blossom tree dried up.
[CHIYOMARU] I wonder
what's going to happen
to our village now.
It's gonna be fine!
Master Sojobo will pull
through like a champ,
and everything'll
go back to normal.
Really?
[NANAMI]
Mm-hm.
You lie. Brother Jiro
insisted that Master Sojobo
would not live very much longer.
So, Brother Jiro is probably
going to become the
fourth successor.
Yet, even if he does prevail,
is that really going
to fix everything?
[DAIDAIMARU whines]
[CHIYOMARU]
What if we never see
the eternal cherry blossom
tree bloom again?
[NANAMI]
I can try my powers.
But I don't think they're gonna
do much against this awful fog.
But at the very least,
I can lift the cloud
hanging over these boys.
Please help me.
[NANAMI gasps]
[BROTHERS gasp]
It bloomed! There are
flowers on the tree again!
Is this real?
Or are we daydreaming?
Oh believe me, this is no dream.
I see what you mean.
What a beautiful tree!
[bell sounds]
That's the evening bell!
We'd better get a move on, huh?
It's our turn to make dinner.
Yeah! But when we get there,
we have to tell everyone
about this miracle!
[CHIYOMARU]
So, what could we say you are?
A celestial nymph from the
heavens who showed up
to put an end to our
suffering at last?
Whoa, you've got
some game for a kid!
Now go on and hurry home!
Thank you, my sister.
[DAIDAIMARU laughs]
[NANAMI]
This made my day.
[gasps] What?
[NANAMI]
The petals are blowing away.
It's no use.
My powers aren't strong
enough to make it last.
We really need Master Sojobo
to bounce back soon.
[NANAMI gasps]
[NARRATOR] And thus,
a would-be mountain god
encountered a celestial nymph.
[NARRATOR] Oh, dear!
Someone's got quite the temper!
Will they be able to
ditch Jiro's guard
to go visit the Sojobo?
Is Nanami's plan foolproof?
Mister Tomoe, what the
devil's gotten into you?
Next time,
"The God Sneaks In".
Stealthily, sneakily,
off on a mad dash!