[NARRATOR]
I don't have a clue.
I feel so humiliated
I could die.
Well? C'mon, what's our plan?
Would it not be easier for us to
dispose of Jiro altogether?
No way!
I'll go look for
Mister Sojobo,
and I'll take Botanmaru with me.
[laughs] I just had a
brilliant idea! I'm so smart!
Oh, share it with us, Nanami!
Now then,
where may I find Jiro?
So the letter was
in good faith.
Oh, right. Now it's
all up to us.
We've got to find the Sojobo.
Let's do it!
Could their plan possibly work?
What fate lies in store for
Nanami and her friends?
Pins and needles, bated breath!
Shinjuro, attended
by a real familiar.
I must say, I never thought
such a pitiful failure
would return to us as a god.
Quite impressive.
It's lovely to see
you too, Brother.
I understand that my
father collapsed recently.
Tell me, where might he be?
He's inside the sanctum,
although he's extremely ill,
so allowing his delinquent
son to see him is impossible.
So, 'land god' or whatever
you call yourself, you are
no longer part of Kurama,
regardless of your name!
[TOMOE] This brute is
the one known as Jiro.
True to tale, he has
the physique of a bear.
And he laid those boorish
hands on Nanami!
I will admit that our past
is somewhat checkered,
but let's forgive and forget.
I am here today to help
you celebrate your succession
to become the Fourth
Sojobo, Brother.
As tribute, I come bearing
a libation from the Heavens.
It would be an honor if you
shared a drink with me.
How lofty of you.
[KURAMA]
This is pure rotgut.
The highest proof booze you
can get from the mundane world.
If you're a lightweight,
it's one, two, three, floor!
You think I'm a lightweight?
I can handle it;
I'm a water god!
I'll drink you under the table!
[KURAMA]
Cheers, you bastard.
Since you are claiming
to be a god,
you must be familiar with the
celestial nymph I met recently.
Beneath the tree.
[TOMOE]
Celestial what?
[KURAMA]
The who?
I'm not. It could've been
anyone. Who knows?
All right, fine then.
Lest we forget,
this sacred mountain
forbids any and all women.
Celestial nymph or not, I intend
to teach her a harsh lesson.
[TOMOE]
Troglodyte.
[slurping]
[NANAMI]
Wow!
This has to be about the
biggest building I've ever seen!
There are no other
tengus around anywhere.
Plus, I feel like we've
passed the same spot
a million times already.
So, uh, is everything all right?
Are we actually making
decent headway here?
Hey, Botanmaru?
Yes we are, okay?
Follow me,
and it'll be all right!
I promise you!
We will get there!
Okay, okay!
Chill out.
[MAMORU]
What a bunch of bull!
[BOTANMARU groans]
You're lost,
admit it, you twerp!
Mamoru!
[BOTANMARU grunts]
Don't call me that!
Uh, this entire compound
is surrounded
by that Jiro guy's barrier.
I can smell the rotten stink
of his aura on everything.
The fox and his friend need
to break Jiro's focus.
Until then, we're
gonna be stuck here.
[NANAMI]
Come on guys.
Please, you've gotta hurry!
I'm finding your heavenly
potion rather pleasant.
What's the matter, Shinjuro?
There's still a great
deal of it left, you know.
So how are you feeling
now, Brother? Good?
[JIRO]
Of course.
[KURAMA chuckles]
Were you planning to get me
drunk so you could exact
some sort of pathetic revenge?
This must be disappointing.
Unlike your feeble spirit,
I am not one to be
corrupted by mere alcohol.
Inebriation is just another
sad form of weakness.
You're the one who
insisted we drink.
You will finish the
entire bottle with me.
[TOMOE] This has gone
far enough, Master Jiro.
[JIRO]
Huh?!
[TOMOE]
In lieu of my Lord and Master,
I, Tomoe, will keep you company.
In deference to your wishes.
Why not let a celestial
nymph pour for you?
[JIRO screams]
[NANAMI, MAMORU, BOTANMARU gasp]
What?
The barrier was rippling.
The caster just lost his focus!
But why?
Who cares, let's make some
fast tracks while we can.
Is there a problem?
You look shaken.
And you were speaking so
confidently earlier, too.
Was it you beneath the eternal
cherry blossom tree then?
Tell me the truth.
I was worried that my arm
was going to break in half.
You are entirely too violent,
especially in the way
you treat women.
[grunts] A woman?
Oh, please!
[TOMOE]
What?
[JIRO] You're merely
disguised as a woman.
I know a man when I see one!
[TOMOE]
How rude!
If you do not believe what I'm
saying, come see for yourself.
Then you will know
which one I am.
[JIRO grunts]
[TOMOE]
I knew it.
Jiro has fallen for her.
[NANAMI] Amazing! The
webbing of the barrier
was all over the place before,
but it's disappeared.
This is the best chance we have.
Let's go, quietly,
or they'll hear us coming!
[YATORI sighs]
That bad omen has come to pass.
It's obvious I must find
Master Jiro immediately.
Sir? Mister Sojobo?
Master Sojobo, we're here!
[NANAMI, BOTANMARU]
Huh?!
[NANAMI]
Is this really him?
He looks, um, kind of frozen.
Lady Nanami!
Get the Peach Pills, quick!
Oh! I got 'em here.
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
--Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
--[NANAMI] Hang on, one second.
[MAMORU] Those aren't
gonna make him better.
[NANAMI, BOTANMARU]
Uh?
That tengu boss has had his
soul taken from his body.
I don't think he'll be
waking up anytime soon.
Not till it gets
returned to him.
Who would do that, though?
Why would they even need it?
[gasps]
[NANAMI]
A black feather? And it's huge.
Jiro!
[YATORI] It's exhausting
being right all the time.
[NANAMI gasps]
[TOMOE]
Women's intuition is strong.
Your point?
I can tell that you have
a little crush on me.
Everything you said
before gives it away.
[grunts] Nonsense!
Women are taboo here,
and I am violating that rule.
Yet you still have
not kicked me out, Jiro.
That is preposterous!
What could I possibly find
alluring about you at all?
[TOMOE]
Ah. This man is infuriating.
As if I, Jiro, could be led
astray by a lowly woman!
[JIRO grunts]
Then look at me.
Prove yourself and give
me a piece of your mind.
[JIRO gasping]
[TOMOE] When you saw
that "celestial nymph"
under the eternal tree, it was
already game over for you.
[JIRO grunts]
How dare you. I would never!
Sorceress! You are attempting
to use your wiles on me!
Hypocrite! Shut up!
If you are such a tough guy,
then practice what you preach,
man up and confess your true
feelings for Nanami!
I cannot stand to
see you like this.
'Tis much like looking into a
mirror, which makes me livid.
[JIRO gasps] Nanami. So,
that is the girl's name.
How enchanting.
[YATORI]
Master Jiro.
What in the world
have you been doing?
Your protective barrier
has been compromised.
[JIRO]
Yatori!
I did warn you about this.
And sure enough,
a couple of rats have gnawed
their way inside the compound.
[JIRO]
Uh.
[YATORI]
Two tengus and one monkey.
They seem pretty shady to me.
But not to worry, I locked 'em
up inside the basement for now.
If we apply some
not-so-gentle pressure,
I'll bet they spill the beans
about working with these guys.
[KURAMA]
Tomoe, stop!
I beg your pardon, but I really
don't have the slightest idea
what you might
be accusing us of.
For my familiar's behavior,
I offer you a sincere apology.
After all, he was
just a wild fox once.
He doesn't know any better.
If you see fit to punish him,
you have my complete permission.
Beat him, torture him,
grill him. I have no preference.
Take your pick.
[KURAMA screams]
You idiot! Can't believe this!
We got pinched, thanks to that
stupid little stunt you pulled!
That's the last time I ever
let you 'help' me with anything!
If you had not stopped me,
I would have ripped that
caveman to shreds
and this ordeal would
be over by now!
That was never part of the plan!
Why isn't any of this sinking
into your fuzzy, pointed skull?
Nanami has been caught, ergo
the plan must change, imbecile!
No obstacle will hinder me.
I will get to her.
Even if I have to chew
my way through this.
[yelps]
Oh, forget it. Jiro made
this cage ironclad.
Yokai powers won't do a damn
thing to break these bars.
There has to be a better game
plan to get us out of here.
[TOMOE]
Finding Nanami and the others
is of critical importance.
I hope you understand
that fully eclipses
saving your father.
That's fine, I don't really care
about saving him anyway.
Honestly, we've barely ever
said two words to each other.
What matters is this.
That freak told us our friends
have been put in the dungeon.
So we need to figure out
a way to rescue them.
[NANAMI groaning]
My head.
--[NANAMI] Wait. Where are we?
--[MAMORU chirps]
Botanmaru!
C'mon, wake up!
[BOTANMARU grunts]
[door opens]
[NANAMI, MAMORU gasp]
[door creaks, foot steps]
[YATORI] These are the rats
who breached our security,
Master Jiro.
[JIRO] Heh. My, my,
look what we have here.
It seems I was nearly
bested by vermin.
--[BOTANMARU groans]
--[NANAMI] Jiro.
I had my suspicion Shinjuro was
plotting something deceitful,
but I never imagined we had
a turncoat living among us.
Botanmaru!
[BOTANMARU whimpers]
[JIRO]
Cursed weakling!
Can you hear me? Botanmaru!
Speak up, now! What is it you've
been snooping around for?
[exhales] Beating up on such
a small, defenseless child.
How can you possibly
think that you deserve
to become the fourth Sojobo?
[JIRO] The way to avoid pain
is strength, that is all.
His weakness is to blame.
That is why he cannot fly even
though he is already seven.
If you can't live without
someone's coddling...
...death is the only solution.
[NANAMI]
What?
[NANAMI] It doesn't matter
how strong you are.
Not even you can go through
life all by yourself.
Or do you expect us to believe
that you've lived on
the mountain for all these years
without any help from anybody?
[JIRO grunts]
Watch your mouth!
What do you know, boy?
[NANAMI]
I know everything.
Even about how you stole
the Sojobo's soul from him.
His soul? You are
not making sense.
[NANAMI]
It wasn't him?
Now, now, Master Jiro. Enough
with the lengthy inquisition.
If you will,
leave everything to Yatori.
You run along and deal
with Master Shinjuro,
and that pesky fox you
captured, 'kay?
[NANAMI]
Tomoe and Kurama?
[JIRO]
Hmph.
And try not to let those
lustful thoughts
sidetrack you this
time, loverboy.
[JIRO]
Uh! Damn it.
[YATORI] Good luck,
we're all counting on you!
[NANAMI]
He had no idea.
If it wasn't Jiro who pulled
out the Sojobo's soul,
--who could it have been?
--[door slams]
Now then. I was certain
the Sojobo's condition
would never
be discovered.
I pegged you as a simple tengu,
but clearly you had me fooled.
Hold on, so you're the one
who did that to him? Why?
Lemme think. I suppose I could
tell you before you die.
Okay, so, there's this guy
I know who trusted me
to get him an obedient
army, right?
Well, these mountain birds
are desperate to follow anyone.
The boss makes the orders.
Baa, baa sheep follow!
A vertical society,
simple and exclusive.
They were the perfect solution!
You're awful!
How did you get away
with something so evil?
It went a little like this.
Correspondence from
your son, Sir.
I was requested to deliver
it to you in person
without being witnessed.
You must be so overwrought.
How could you not be;
he is your beloved only son!
[SOJOBO]
Yatori, was it?
Yes, Sojobo?
[SOJOBO] I consider all
the tengus of this mountain
to be my children.
I purposefully drew
a distinction between them,
and my own son, Shinjuro,
[SOJOBO] However, I treasure
them, all of them, equally.
[YATORI] Yes. He left
himself utterly vulnerable.
I couldn't believe he fell
for such a cheap trick;
it was almost too easy.
[NANAMI gasps]
[BOTANMARU]
You're horrible!
This is the part where
we conclude our chitchat.
My report to Master
Jiro will be that,
after having failed
in your mission,
you took your own lives.
--[BOTANMARU yelps]
--[NANAMI] What. I can't move!
[YATORI] Welcome to your
final resting pla-! [gasps]
We'll see about that, pal.
[YATORI]
Hm?
[NANAMI]
Here's the deal.
[MAMORU squeaks]
You're evil! And evil
must pay! Mamoru, go!
[MAMORU squeaks]
What? No way! Stop!
This can't be happening!
Barrier against evil!
[YATORI screams]
[JIRO] I will get stronger.
Much more than I already am.
I've gotten taller
than the others,
and my back and legs are so
solid that when I grow up,
I'm going to have the biggest
wings of anyone on the mountain.
The Brothers all agreed.
[JIRO] If I train harder than
ever, I might become number one.
[SOJOBO]
Jiro.
Jiro!
[JIRO]
Uh?
[SOJOBO]
It's commendable,
to spend so much
extra time training.
[JIRO]
Thank you, Master Sojobo!
[SOJOBO] I hear you won
brilliantly for the first time
in the sword-fighting
competition yesterday.
I am beaming with pride,
although I am afraid you cannot
see it under my huge beard.
Still, you should not
push yourself too hard,
and jeopardize your health, so I
pronounce you done for the day.
Yes, sir!
[JIRO] Master Sojobo. The
strongest tengu on the mountain.
I am now that tengu,
and yet, I feel no pride.
I'm starting to see
the celestial nymph,
even in that four-eyed boy.
It doesn't matter
how strong you are.
Not even you can go through
life all by yourself.
[JIRO]
Damn it!
I am about to become
the Sojobo of Kurama.
Why can't I be happy about that?
[BOYS giggle]
[DAIDAIMARU groans]
[crash]
Are you okay? Daidaimaru.
Mm. Oh, Master Jiro!
[CHIYOMARU]
Huh!
Why you... clumsy fools!
Pay attention to where
you are walking!
[CHIYOMARU, TAKEMARU]
My apologies, sir!
--[DAIDAIMARU cries]
--[JIRO] Uh?
[CHIYOMARU, TAKEMARU whimper]
[JIRO]
Uh...
[DAIDAIMARU sobbing]
[NANAMI] Or do you expect us
to believe that you've lived on
the mountain for all these years
without any help from anybody?
Please put me down! I realize
you're rightfully upset with me,
but why don't you be reasonable?
I'm really kind of
hating it up here!
Tell us where the Sojobo's
soul is, right this second!
[chuckles] I have it hidden
deep within this compound.
No one can find it if I'm gone.
So if you're attempting to get
rid of me, best of luck
ever solving that mystery
and bringing him
back to the living!
[YATORI screams]
[BOTANMARU] So that was
a barrier against evil.
Master Jiro's barrier
is still here,
but Nanami made that man
fly away like a piece of paper!
That is the scariest lady
I've ever seen!
Come on. We gotta find
that missing soul,
so shake your tailfeather!
We'll use this white talisman.
It'll do all the
hard work for us!
I was afraid it wouldn't be
much help in here,
since Jiro's barrier
is so tough!
But why?
It seems like your
barrier against evil
was working just fine!
[NANAMI gasps]
That's it!
[BOTANMARU]
Uh...
We're inside Jiro's
barrier, right?
So, if everything
inside it is his,
I just need to figure out a
way that I can make it mine.
[DAIDAIMARU crying]
What are you crying about now?
This is tiresome.
Forgive him, he means no harm.
He isn't feeling
very well today,
Master Jiro, so we were taking
him back to his room.
[CHIYOMARU]
Please don't punish him.
I would rather take the blame!
[SUIRO]
You must stop this, Jiro!
[JIRO gasps]
[JIRO]
Suiro.
[DAIDAIMARU whimpers]
[JIRO]
Hmph. 'Tis pointless.
Master Jiro, there is trouble!
What is it?
It's terrible.
There is a young woman,
and she's running around
inside the compound!
[JIRO gasps]
[NANAMI]
Get outta my way!
C'mon, c'mon;
move it, step aside!
[NANAMI] I'll cast a bigger
barrier against evil this time.
It should be able
to cancel out Jiro's.
This whole compound'll be
surrounded with my power,
not his!
[MAMORU squeaks]
[COMMON TENGU C]
Where did she go?
She went straight
towards the West Hall!
The West Hall?
[COMMON TENGU C gasp]
Master Jiro!
[JIRO] Towards the Sanctum
where Shinjuro and the fox
are locked up.
Must be that nymph.
Look down! Where the
woman just passed by.
It's sparkling gold!
Like it's made of stars.
[COMMON TENGU E]
Wow, that's pretty.
[COMMON TENGU D]
Sh! Moron.
Keep your voice down,
Jiro's right there!
Wake up, foxy.
The tengu guarding us
just randomly took
off in a huge hurry.
I have no clue what
might have happened,
but it seems like now is the
perfect time to escape.
Why don't you come
up with something?
I know it must be hard
with your tiny brain.
Oh, how rich.
At least I have a brain,
you damn cretin!
No you don't!
Have you looked at yourself;
your ears are twice the
size of your head!
I don't understand how you
manage to stand up straight!
Can you even hear me through
that hair, mountain fowl?
[BOTANMARU] Master Shinjuro!
I finally found you!
I have come to rescue you!
Oh, good.
Well done, Botanmaru.
Glad you're safe and sound.
My goodness! This is a very
impressive barrier prison.
I don't think I can get
you out of it by myself!
I need some more help!
This sucks.
Where has Nanami gone?
Why have you separated from her?
Is she all right?
She is currently running about,
casting a barrier against evil
around the whole compound.
[TOMOE]
The whole compound?
It seems Master Sojobo is even
worse than we thought!
We've gotta help him!
Nanami and I found him locked
away in the innermost sanctum!
His soul was taken by a
scary yokai called Yatori,
and now he looks as if he's
been turned into stone!
So the entire story we heard
about him being sick
was never even true!
What?
[BOTANMARU] Believe it!
Yatori told us everything.
He said he hid Master Sojobo's
soul in the most secret place
in the compound and nobody
would ever find it.
It was all a selfish plot
to overthrow the Third
and take control of Kurama.
Where is this light coming from?
I'm not sure where it came from,
but our prison is fading away.
It's Nanami's barrier.
She has succeeded.
I knew she could do it.
[NANAMI]
All right.
[NARRATOR]
Nanami's handiwork
made the compound
look like glitter!
She's really come
into her own.
Cool, we're going to find
the Sojobo's soul!
But Jiro's learned the truth
and gone to hunt for it himself.
We can't let him win
this game of hide and seek!
Next time, "The God Receives
a Romantic Confession".
Whoa! Come again?