[AKURA-OH]
Hey.
Have you heard the phrase
"sea of fire" before?
It means a fire that
behaves like the sea.
I'm curious to see
this adage in action.
If we ignite everything here,
as far as the eye can see
out to the horizon's edge,
we could create a sea of fire.
[TOMOE]
Do not strain yourself.
[AKURA-OH]
Mm?
Any moron can set a fire,
but it takessomeone far
more skilled to quench it.
Do not fiddle with flame if you
lack power to control it,
Akura-oh. If you are
so hot for a sea ablaze,
I will show you an
ocean of fox-fire.
It will put what you are
imagining to pure shame.
Believe you me.
[KIRIHITO'S MOTHER] Kirihito?
Are you awake?
Are you feeling any better,
dear? Do you mind if I come in?
You haven't eaten anything
since this morning, right?
Well, it's time for dinner. Uh!
Look at you!
The color has come back
to your face again.
It's your favorite; sautéed
liver and garlic chives.
Boys need to eat a lot in order
to build up their strength.
If you don't eat you won't
heal as quickly. Okay?
Oh, dear, your hand is so cold.
Did you forget to
turn on the heat?
I've told you.
I'm very busy at the moment.
You don't need to
prepare my meals for me.
Leave me alone,
mother. Go away.
[KIRIHITO'S MOTHER gasps]
Not so fast.
I'm sorry for interrupting
your studies. But...
Meals are a different story.
And this one is no exception.
Once you're done,
you can leave the plates
out in the hallway for me.
Damn. She never
stops nagging me.
[KIKUICHI]
Aw, yeah!
Is this organ meat,
Master Kirihito?
[MONJIRO] Liver and chives!
Liver and chives!
[AKURA-OH] They sealed
off Yomotsu Hirasaka,
but I've found a better way
into the Netherworld.
Fortunately, I was able to
make a stone mirror
with soil I brought
back with me.
When this device matches
up with the frequency
of the Netherworld, the
entrance should be complete.
And soon enough,
the door will open.
I'm making my way
back down there again
and this time,
I will get my old body back!
The two of you can stay here.
When Shikigami and Yokai come in
contact with that environment,
they turn to dust.
[KIKUICHI]
But, Master!
Are you sure you'll be
all right traveling alone?
Yes.
[AKURA-OH]
The girl's hair. This is my key.
[YATORI] Heading to
the battlefield, are we?
[AKURA-OH]
Uh?
[YATORI]
How incredibly brave of you.
I would absolutely love
it if you took me to
the Netherworld with you;
I could do with a thrill!
[MONJIRO, KIKUICHI growl]
[MONJIRO] You! You're that
shifty little weasel
--from before!
--[YATORI] Ah!
[KIKUICHI]
What are you doing here?
Guys, I know how
you feel, believe me.
I'm really embarrassed
about dropping the ball
with that business
on Kurama.
[AKURA-OH] You're pathetic.
You talk such a big game,
and then you come back here
with nothing to show for it.
That's gutsy, Yatori.
I'm so flattered. Oh, you
actually remember who I am!
[YATORI]
Master Kirihito!
[AKURA-OH] Obviously. Do
you think I'm stupid enough
to forget the name of
a potential enemy?
[YATORI laughs]
[KIKUICHI]  Master Kirihito!
The stone mirror is opening!
[AKURA-OH]
It's finally about to happen!
[YATORI]
Master Kirihito, please!
I wanna go with you so badly!
[KIKUICHI]
No way!
[AKURA-OH]
It's all right.
[KIKUICHI]
What?
Have it your way.
If you can keep up with me.
[AKURA-OH] The underground world
of stench and defilement.
Those who cannot bear
the poisonous atmosphere
turn to dust.
Slumbering somewhere in the
depths is my empty body.
And I will get it back.
[YATORI sighs]
It's huge.
So, this is the Netherworld.
[YATORI] I never imagined that
it was so hot down here. Huh?
I wonder where Master Kirihito
ended up landing. Uh. Oh?
[YATORI]
Master Kirihito!
There you are!
I wouldn't know what to do
if I couldn't find you.
[AKURA-OH] Well, this is
unexpected. You're still alive.
[YATORI]
Huh?
Yokai of the weak persuasion
turn to dust when they
touch Netherworld air.
I'd hoped the same thing
might happen to you,
just like it did to Tekkimaru.
Who are you, really? And what's
your interest in Akura-oh?
Well, I, uh...
I actually used to serve Master
Akura-oh a long time ago.
[AKURA-OH]
I don't know this guy.
Don't lie to me,
or you will pay.
[YATORI]
But it's true.
Listen, the truth is Master
Akura-oh might
have a hard time
remembering me.
It's because I was a shy kid,
always off crying by
myself in a corner.
You seem young, Master Kirihito,
so I doubt you ever
had the pleasure of knowing
the esteemed Master.
To put it mildly, he possesses
a spirit of total depravity.
He takes what he wants,
when he wants,
and couldn't care less how
it affects anybody else.
And even though he didn't care,
most of his underlings
still followed him around
wherever he went! I was lucky
enough to be one of them.
Hey, are you listening to me?
[AKURA-OH]
It's hot.
His only friend was a fox!
They always traveled together,
no matter what.
[AKURA-OH gasping]
[YATORI] Wherever the two went,
no yokai posed a threat to them.
They were so powerful together
that even the mighty gods
could only stand by and watch.
However, at some point,
Master Akura-oh and
the fox grew estranged.
And it was all
downhill from there.
The fox disappeared,
and Master Akura-oh's body
went to the Netherworld.
[AKURA-OH seethes]
Can you guess what the
disagreement was all about?
[AKURA-OH] It was because
the fox got stupid.
That vulpine fool
became infatuated
with some silly human girl, and
deluded himself into thinking
he was going to
become human as well,
just so he could be "happy"!
Ah!
I will make hamburger steak
today, Nanami's favorite!
Wait, do you actually know how
to make something that fancy?
[TOMOE] Yes. The recipe says
it is actually quite simple.
And the flavor will disguise
the shiitake that are going in.
Ah! That's so mean!
Nanami hates shiitake mushrooms!
I wanna help!
I'm gonna add
this lizard's tail.
I wanna make sure that Nanami
has all of the energy she needs.
A gecko! A turtle!
And a salamander, too!
[NANAMI]
Hey! What's up, you slacker?
I know you haven't finished
cleaning the storehouse yet!
Oh! Nanami!
The new year is just around
the corner, you know.
[MIZUKI laughs]
Yes, ma'am.
Mm. You're making hamburger
steak? Yay, I can't wait!
[YATORI]
I see your point.
It appears that the fox has
definitely turned soft
over the years.
Mercy, I am wilting!
Where do you figure we are now?
It feels like we've been
wandering for days on end.
Master Akura-oh's body can't be
that much farther away from us.
Maybe I'm hallucinating, but
it seems to be getting hotter.
How are you not melting?
[AKURA-OH]
Found it.
[YATORI]
Ah?
[AKURA-OH]  My body. I can
hardly believe it was abandoned
in such a wretched place.
Wow! That's amazing!
Is that a mountain of fire?
[AKURA-OH]
No question about it.
My body is at the top
of that mountain.
I'd guess this is
the Netherworld's
de facto dumping ground.
The gods must use
this place to incinerate
undesirable entities that are
too much for them to handle.
[AKURA-OH grunts]
[YATORI]
Master Kirihito?
[AKURA-OH] But not even
a towering inferno like this
could burn my body to ash.
I'll just keep self-regenerating
over and over, for all eternity.
[AKURA-OH]
My body.
[YATORI]
Get hold of yourself!
[AKURA-OH gasps]
Now that we know
what the situation is,
we should leave
and call it a day.
I'm afraid if we stay
here too much longer,
you'll shrivel up into a husk.
Don't be ridiculous.
It is within my reach!
Whether you like it or not,
we aren't immortal.
And we cannot climb this
mountain safely. Unless...
If you have some way
to quench the flames,
that would be different.
[AKURA-OH gasps]
[AKURA-OH]
Tomoe! Damn him!
This is all his fault,
and I loathe him from
the depths of my soul.
But I can't retrieve my body.
Not without his help.
[KIKUICHI, MONJIRO gasp]
Whew, we made
it home in one piece.
[KIKUICHI]
Master Kirihito!
Just hang in there!
You'll be fine!
[MONJIRO] What did you do
to Master Kirihito, hoodlum?
Oh, please. I did nothing.
[AKURA-OH chuckles]
[YATORI, MONJIRO]
Huh?!
I won't get that bastard's help.
No need to be short-sighted
when there's a much better
way to look at it. Hm.
Whatever it takes,
if it's useful, I'll use it.
End of story! If it means
I get my body back,
I'll do anything necessary
to make it happen!
Great!
[MONJIRO gasps]
Master Kirihito,
there's black smoke coming
out of the stone mirror!
[AKURA-OH]
oison from the Netherworld?
Why would it be leaking out?
[MONJIRO screams]
[KIKUICHI]
Monjiro!
Master, we must close the
hole to the Netherworld!
No chance.
The connecting aperture
can't be sealed
without shattering
the stone mirror.
[AKURA-OH] I finally got this
entrance to the Netherworld
opened, I won't
destroy it now.
I'm getting my original
body back from down there,
no matter what it takes.
And to that end,
this place being
exposed to the poison
is no skin off my back,
so to speak.
I'm unaffected.
Not my problem.
[KIRIHITO'S MOTHER]
Kirihito?
[AKURA-OH gasping]
Uh. Hi, honey!
Are your studies going well?
We received some sweet peaches.
Would you like
a late-night snack?
Look, I told you,
I'm too busy right now.
[AKURA-OH]
Thank you, Mother.
A wedding, huh?
[MIZUKI]
Hm? Sorry, what?
Are you saying that
you're interested in one?
[NANAMI] Yeah. In fact,
I've gotten a proposal already.
[MIZUKI]
Ah!
If Tomoe's oaky with it,
I think that I'm actually
going to accept.
[TOMOE] Ever since we
descended from Mount Kurama,
I have felt constant
needling pain in my chest.
[KOTETSU] Master Tomoe. You must
go to the Lord Year God's place
before the new
year arrives.
We need to receive a
new talisman, and soon.
Oh, is it time for that already?
A word, fox!
A lowly familiar
proposing marriage
to his lady and mistress should
die ten thousand deaths!
You, outside! Now!
[TOMOE huffs] As usual,
your words are a mystery to me,
which hardly matters.
For now I will skin you like
the slimy serpent you are!
[roaring]
[NANAMI]
Stop it!
Honestly. Where did
you get the stupid idea
that I'm the one who's
getting married?
So you aren't getting hitched?
Of course not! I just
received a proposal
asking me to host
a wedding at the shrine.
I see, from whom?
[NANAMI]
Himemiko of the Swamp!
Ludicrous! A catfish
cannot marry a human!
Well, how would you know
unless you give it a
chance, you killjoy!
Himemiko told me that when
she and Kotaro are ready
for the big day, they would love
to hold the ceremony here!
To be there from when they met,
up to when they get married
would be so amazing!
They are playing house,
but planning matrimony.
Not to mention an
interspecies one at that.
I fear your immaturity
disqualifies you for this.
Don't care! I'm doing it!
I'm making really good
progress as a god,
in case you hadn't noticed!
Yeah, I have faith that you
can totally pull it off.
And even if Tomoe
won't cooperate,
don't worry, you can
always count on me.
Thanks, you're so awesome!
[TOMOE]
Wanton reptile.
Oh, good. I am so relieved.
I totally thought you were
gonna change your mind
and renounce your land god
status to get married.
Uh-uh.
It's never gonna be me walking
down the aisle. Don't worry.
[KOTETSU] Master Tomoe,
you must get ready soon.
If you do not hurry to
the Lord Year God's shrine,
the gates will close,
and we will miss our chance.
Ah. Indeed, you are correct.
Hold on a sec.
Are you talking about that
god you always have to go
visit on New Year's Day?
Yes,'tis also the
one who bestows
abundance and fortune
on each new year.
There was only one,
the original,
who had taken on the entire
enterprise by himself.
Though being overworked took
its toll and he hurt his back.
Since then, twelve different
gods alternate each year
to serve in that capacity
and share the onus.
Therefore, it has
become customary
to pay a call to the Year
God's shrine annually
in order to receive
a brand new talism
from the subsequent
Year God. And on that note,
the time has come for the two
of us to be on our merry way
to the shrine for that
very same reason.
[MIZUKI]
Hm?
Is there any chance that the
"us" only refers to you and me?
How sharp you are.
That is exactly what it means.
What do you say we tend
to unfinished business
with some rare privacy? Just
a couple of old familiars, eh?
You guys are going alone?
When are you coming back?
Gee, there is a chance
that Mizuki may not
be able to return.
And I do mean forever.
No, no; I think
that would be Tomoe.
[NANAMI]
Huh? Then, I'm going too.
Incorrect.
Wherever you go,
bedlam is certain to follow.
I said I'm going!
[TOMOE]
Mm.
Sounds good!
[TOMOE]
Here we go.
This is always
the case with her.
Oblivious to her limits,
she wants to stick
her nose in everything.
Wow. This is really
the Year God's shrine?
[MIZUKI]
Well, the entrance, at least.
[NANAMI]
There are so many torii gates.
We just have to
pass through, right?
What the-? This one has my
name written on it. But why?
The Torii Gates of Twelve are
designed to share the past
twelve years with the Year God
to inform him of the time missed
since last he served.
Those who pay a visit
to this particular shrine
must pass through these gates
to reflect upon their own dozen
years as ritual necessity.
I truly dread this
part of the trip.
It always makes my
head feel spiny.
Wait, you mean it
makes you feel dizzy?
I call it the
'twelve-year hangover'.
You are to remain here, Nanami.
The snake and I will go,
complete our business,
and return tout suite.
An abrupt shift of consciousness
can be very dangerous
for humans.
I'll be fine! Besides,
it seems kinda cool!
You just have to go
through the torii gate
with your name on it, right?
[TOMOE]
Not again.
[MIZUKI]
And off she goes. I envy Nanami.
She has such a free soul, she
never worries about anything.
I'm scared.
I don't want to relive those
years after I lost Lady Yonomori
and I was nothing
but a lonely shut-in.
Nanami does define
'devil-may-care'.
Here's the real irony,
she is free.
Free to do anything she wants,
except for marrying you,
and she accepts it
willingly. Smart girl.
Unfortunately,
she cannot hold a candle
to you at being manipulative.
You're amazing, Tomoe!
I mean, you know
Nanami so incredibly well!
[TOMOE growls]
I'm really not digging
the vibe here anymore. Bye!
[TOMOE]
It is true though.
I probably know her better
than anyone ever has.
Her habits. Her mannerisms.
Even her sweet essence.
Yes.
Tomoe. Nanami went in
there a while ago,
but she still hasn't
come out yet.
[TOMOE] Why do I already feel
something troublesome afoot?
Oh, right because
I predicted this.
[MIZUKI]
Don't yell at her, okay?
It is very likely
her consciousness
has become stuck somewhere.
You do know it's
forbidden to pass
through someone
else's gate, right?
'Tis too late, snake.
Where do we suppose
Nanami's consciousness is?
[MIZUKI] I wouldn't even
know where to start.
[GIRL panting]
[giggling]
[MIZUKI]
Tomoe!
Why are you just standing there?
That was little Nanami!
[TOMOE]
Huh?!
It looks like her consciousness
has gone back
twelve years in time!
[TOMOE gasps]
[TOMOE]
No, impossible.
[NANAMI'S FATHER]
Nanami.
[NANAMI]
Huh?!
On your way home from school?
Hi, Daddy!
[NANAMI'S FATHER]
What'cha got there?
I have a bag of bread crust!
I'm bringing it home to Mommy.
[NANAMI'S FATHER laughs]
I've got something
you'll like better. Look!
Ah! Chocolate!
Yummy! Yay! Yay!
[NANAMI'S FATHER] I won
it at the pachinko parlor.
It's a prize, just for you!
--[NANAMI'S FATHER] Gotta go.
--[NANAMI] Huh?
[NANAMI'S FATHER]
I finally hit the big time,
so let Mom know I won't
be back for a while.
[NANAMI laughs]
[MIZUKI]
Nanami!
There you are!
The tiny version of you
is so cute, too!
C'mon. Let's go home, okay?
[NANAMI]
Mm.
--[MIZUKI groans]
--[NANAMI] Kidnapper!
[NANAMI panting]
[MIZUKI]
Stop.
That is definitely her.
I told you, didn't I?
Of course it is!
[TOMOE] She acts beyond her
limits, and even at this age,
she is equal parts
reckless and crazy.
Not only that, but she has
this way of scampering about.
I find it adorable.
[TOMOE]
Whatever the case,
I must hasten to bring
Nanami back home.
[NANAMI'S MOTHER]
You have my deepest apologies!
Come on! Are you gonna pay up
or what? I saw your husband
hanging around the pachinko
parlor this morning.
If you've got the money
for gambling games,
then you can damn well pay us!
P.S. You're two whole months
behind on the rent now!
[NANAMI'S MOTHER]
I'm so sorry.
I promise, I'll have my husband
pay you all by Monday for sure.
[BILL COLLECTOR]
Like I believe that!
This isn't the first time we've
had to ask you to pay up!
[BILL COLLECTOR, LANDLORD
shouting]
[LANDLORD] You barely have
a yen to your name anyway.
[shouting continues]
[LANDLORD] I was nice
enough to rent to you.
[BILL COLLECTOR] If you can't
pay up, don't live here.
[shouting continues]
[BILL COLLECTOR]
We have to make a living, too.
[LANDLORD] Everyone else'll
ask me to cut them slack.
[NANAMI'S MOTHER] I swear I
will have the money by Monday.
Yes, of course.
[BILL COLLECTOR]
I mean it!
[NANAMI'S MOTHER]
You have my deepest apologies.
Uh?!
Nanami! Good, you're home!
Mommy, hi!
[NANAMI cries]
[TOMOE] Nanami has barely ever
spoken about her parents at all.
Now it makes sense.
Makes sense, my tail.
Let's hurry already.
Her mother is suffering
in secret from a long illness.
It is doubtful she
will live much longer.
[TOMOE]
One crept away in the night.
The other stayed just to die.
[MIZUKI sighs]
Come on, Tomoe.
[TOMOE]
Wait. Just a little longer.
[TOMOE] That-That is a Nanami
I do not know at all.
[NARRATOR]
Tomoe and Mizuki peek
into Nanami's
mysterious childhood.
Such a tempestuous life
for a tot! Can't watch!
But can't look away!
What's on Tomoe's mind as he
gets this close to tiny Nanami?
Next time, "The God Receives
a Marriage Proposal."
It's the last episode!
Watch it and weep!
I know I will.