[NARRATOR] We just have to
pass through these, right?
Yay! Ha, ha.
Tomoe! That was little Nanami!
Mommy!
Her mother is suffering in
secret from a long illness.
It is doubtful she will
live much longer.
[TOMOE] Seeing Nanami at this
tender age is fascinating.
I can hardly recognize her.
[NANAMI]
It's so yummy, mommy!
I'm glad you like it, sweetie!
I'm putting the leftovers
in the freezer
so you can have more later. Uh.
Ah! The money I hid in
the freezer to pay
this month's electric
bill isn't there!
But how? Ah... Curse you.
That was the best hiding spot I
could come up with. [coughs]
Snap! It's my lucky day!
Mommy, do you
feel yucky again?
Oh. I'm all right, don't worry.
I'm sorry, Nanami. Listen to me.
Maybe someday,
mommy's gonna have
to go away for a while.
If that happens,
I need you to be a big girl
and take care of yourself, okay?
You'll have to clean the house
and lock the doors every night.
Will I be all alone?
What about daddy?
What about daddy? Don't you dare
count on that good-for-nothing
father of yours, and do not tell
him where you keep your money!
I don't care if
he begs and cries,
you keep it to
yourself. Capiche?
[NANAMI]
Okay.
My poor little girl.
I wish I could have given
you a brother or a sister.
Our family line has
been entirely female.
Every mother has
had one daughter.
It was like that for me,
and your grandma,
and your great-grandma.
[NANAMI]
Why?
I wanna have a big
brother, mommy!
Oh? But there's more to the
story you haven't heard, yet.
Once upon a time,
so she could be pretty,
one of our sillier ancestors
drank a special beauty potion
given to her by the gods.
Well, ever since then,
each generation of our family
has been blessed with only one
healthy and adorable baby girl.
And you're my one! Look at you!
The prettiest and smartest
girl in our family!
[NANAMI giggles]
But this blessing came at
a price. We've been cursed.
None of us ever found a man
that wasn't worthless!
They've all been deadbeats
that suck the life out of us!
Listen to me, sweetie.
Under no circumstances
can you count on men.
I want you to grow
up big and strong,
and live a long healthy life,
even if that means you have to
stay single to do it. Okay?
Kay! When I get big
I'm gonna stay single
and do everything all by myself!
[NANAMI'S MOTHER]
Great!
[TOMOE] I see. Nanami
inherited her nerves of steel
from her late mother.
Interesting.
Human children all grow up
by watching their parents.
Nanami is no different.
Her parents set the example
of whom she would become.
Can you tell me why
you've become
so comfortable sitting here?
I can understand wanting
to get your fill of this
cute little Nanami.
But you realize, these are just
her memories, none of it's real.
We gain nothing by seeing this.
Meanwhile, she's in pain.
We should lead her back
out of this nightmare.
[TOMOE]
Yes. You are correct.
But even so. I have to see more.
This is a side of her
that I do not know.
[TOMOE]
Just a little longer.
[NANAMI'S FATHER laughs]
[NANAMI'S FATHER snores]
[TOMOE]
Just a little more.
[CHILDREN laughing]
[MOE]
Hey, Emii.
What did you ask Santa
Claus for this year?
Last year I got a new fashion
doll for Christmas from him.
This year I'm asking Santa
for a fashion dream house!
That's so cool!
This year, I'm asking
him for a bicycle!
What about you, Nanami?
[NANAMI]
I'll be okay.
I take care of my house
and keep my money hidden!
I lock all the doors every
night, so no strange man
is gonna get in
while I'm sleeping,
even if he begs and cries!
You should all lock your doors
before you go to sleep, too.
You're weird, Nanami!
Santa Claus brings presents
through the chimney!
You're gonna be on
the naughty list!
I've seen enough!
I can't watch anymore!
The raw emotion is overpowering!
This Santa guy has claws?
You are not helping at all!
Looks like it's up to me!
It's okay, I'll save her.
You sit there, couch potato.
[TOMOE] I am not a potato.
I am learning about Nanami.
No wonder she developed such
spirit; 'tis how she survived.
She surely would've
been crushed
under the weight of
all this without it.
[TOMOE]
The poor girl.
[MIZUKI]
Nanami, dear!
[NANAMI]
Huh?
[MIZUKI]
Long time no see!
[NANAMI]
Hm?
[MIZUKI]
No, don't look at me like that!
I'm here to help you!
I'm Mizuki, your primary
and most loyal familiar!
Don't you recognize me?
Uh. I guess there's no way
you could remember me.
[NANAMI]
I do remember you.
[MIZUKI]
Hm?
Stranger danger!
I should have known.
You've got it all wrong. I'm--
[NANAMI panting]
[NANAMI gasping]
Nice save, Tomoe!
[TOMOE] Quickly.
Come with me. We have to run.
The stranger is closing in.
[MIZUKI]
Hey!
[TOMOE] That is what you get,
you lousy snake.
[MIZUKI] Tomoe.
I'm gonna kill you for that!
[TOMOE]
I swear.
[NANAMI]
Your ears!
They're so funny!
Kinda like a cat's!
Can you hear a lot?
Hey, hey!
[TOMOE] Why did I get
caught up in this mess?
Well, I suppose we
should head for the exit.
--[NANAMI chatting]
--[TOMOE] Hm?
[TOMOE]
The scenery is rather odd.
I had thought it was blurry,
but some parts are
exceedingly detailed.
[TOMOE]
I see.
This is the world
of her memories.
The more she paid attention
to something back then,
the more clearly it appears now.
[TOMOE]
Would you like some ice cream?
No, uh! That's okay, thanks!
[TOMOE]
'Tis alright.
Oh, wow!
That was amazing,
big brother!
[TOMOE]
Uh, big brother?
If there is anything else
you desire, let me know.
I am happy to
fetch it for you.
[TOMOE] In this world,
the things that you long for
are as plain as day. For me,
satisfying those needs
is a simple matter.
[NANAMI]
Wow! Is this really my dinner?
Yes.
For real?
[TOMOE] Anything you want.
If it will help you smile.
[TOMOE]
I am here.
I will stay by your side.
[TOMOE]
There is no need to be sad.
[NANAMI]
Oh. The sun's going down.
[TOMOE]
Her sunset is huge.
[NANAMI] The day's over.
Everybody is gonna go home now.
I don't wanna go home, though.
Back there, nobody
is waiting for me.
I have to be all by myself.
[TOMOE]
I understand.
I know what you truly desire.
Only for the time being.
In a few years,
when you are older,
you will become
the head of a household
more rowdy than you can imagine.
Are you telling me that
I'm gonna get married
when I get bigger?
And then I'm going to make a new
family to replace my old one?
[TOMOE]
Hm? Oh, well, no.
That's good! Because
I'm not getting married!
And why is that?
Because my family has really
bad luck with dead meat men!
I can't count on a husband,
so I'm gonna stay healthy and
single when I get bigger! Uh!
[TOMOE] It is not that
you have bad luck,
but that you are a poor
judge of character.
Take me for example.
I could fill all your
days with happiness.
Anything that you wanted,
I would readily provide.
There could be no one
more dependable than me
for "bringing home the bacon,"
as they say.
[NANAMI]
I get what you're doing!
You can't use yummy
foods to trick me
into a loveless marriage!
So do you really love me?
I need to know.
[TOMOE] When asked in such
a direct and adorable way.
[TOMOE] Yes. How could
I not tell you the truth?
I do love you.
Well, will you marry me, Nanami?
[TOMOE]
Know this.
I will ensure you always
have that carefree
smile on your face.
Okay!
[TOMOE] I will always
stand by your side.
[TOMOE] What in the world
am I going to do?
To have become swept
up in the moment
and proposed to her.
How am going to talk
my way out of this one?
I have truly done it this time.
Tomoe, you asked me
to marry you, right?
[TOMOE]
She is bound to press the issue.
Uh. How can I possibly
get out of this mess?
What is the matter, Tomoe?
You're awfully fidgety.
Don't you worry about a thing,
I can keep a secret
as a fellow familiar.
Nanami will never know what
you did to her as a child.
Wait, seriously?
[MIZUKI] Ah, so you did
do something to her.
[TOMOE growls]
[roaring]
[NANAMI]
Stop!
Geez. Why do you guys fight
every time I turn
my back on you?
Hey, where are we?
What happened to
the Torii Gates?
Well, you're on the
other side of them.
[NANAMI]
Huh? When did we go through?
Can't believe I missed that,
I must have fallen asleep.
It does feel like I woke up
from a really long dream.
Yeah? What kind of dream?
[TOMOE] It would appear
I was worried for nothing.
Even if she did remember
what happened,
Nanami would believe the
proposal was merely a fantasy.
Nothing more.
[NANAMI]
I dunno.
I can't remember anything;
so it must not have
mattered very much.
Really? Are you sure.
Nothing about a sweet,
handsome stranger?
Did you just say "a stranger"?
That doesn't ring any bells.
[TOMOE] Uh! She really
does not remember?
Right! Enough chitchat!
Let's get to the
Year God's shrine,
grab the new talisman,
and go back home!
If we don't hurry,
the sun's gonna set!
[MIZUKI] The entrance should
be around here somewhere.
[NANAMI] I've never met
next year's god before;
I wonder what he's like.
Have you ever met him?
Tomoe?
[TOMOE] Is it true?
Does she really not recall?
Would you like some
ice cream, Nanami?
Hey! Neato where
did that come from?
Ah! Ice cream,
I've missed you!
[NANAMI] Hold on,
you've had ice cream before?
Uh-huh. Back when
we were at the beach!
In that case,
you should have it.
Oh, you don't mind, right?
[TOMOE groans]
[MIZUKI] Can I?
Oh, thank you! Hooray!
[giggles] You're just like a
little kid sometimes, Mizuki.
[TOMOE]
She says with no irony.
Moments ago,
the little kid was her.
Oh that reminds me,
I never knew how much you
take after your mother.
You think I'm like
my mom? I dunno.
I always thought I
took after my dad.
I was really young
when she passed away,
so I hardly knew her.
I can barely even remember
what she looked like.
We lost all the photos
of her in the fire.
It would've been nice if one
had survived, but, oh well.
[TOMOE] It seems twelve
years is enough time
for a human to change.
Little Nanami and
the present one.
Though they are
the same person,
are completely different
from one another. 'Tis sad.
[TOMOE]
How can this be?
What happened to the child?
[NANAMI]
Uh! You okay?
What in the world?
[YEAR GOD]
Hey!
[NANAMI, TOMOE, MIZUKI]
Huh?
[YEAR GOD]
Hey!
[NANAMI]
Mm.
Yo! Are you the human god
from the Mikage Shrine?
Oh, Lord Year God, it's you!
[NANAMI] Wait.
He's the year god?
[YEAR GOD grunts] Sorry I can't
give ya a proper greeting.
I've gotta try and sheer off all
this wool before the new year.
If I don't, we're
gonna have problems.
[NANAMI]
Wool?
[SHEEB baas]
[NANAMI]
What the heck?
[TOMOE]
He is the zodiac sheep.
[MIZUKI]
So this thing is a sheep!
[MIZUKI sighs] Wow!
Hm. I thought it'd be softer.
[YEAR GOD]
I wish.
This dude keeps on
insisting that "the fluff"
is gonna be "all the rage"
next year.
But if I can't get
him trimmed down,
there's no way
he'll fit in the shrine.
[TOMOE]
Then why did you wait
until the last minute
to handle this?
Hey, that reminds me!
If it's not too much trouble,
we've actually come here to
get next year's talisman.
Oh. Yeah, the talisman?
It's in there.
[SHEEP]
Baa?
[NANAMI] Hm?!
Wait, that's your shrine?
[MIZUKI] It's so small!
No wonder he can't fit inside!
He hasn't budged
since this morning,
so I told him it was time for
a haircut, much to his dismay.
[SHEEP]
Baa!
[MIZUKI, NANAMI]
Ah!
No, stop! You're
crushing the shrine!
Too bad it's not softer!
Ah. Well.
[YEAR GOD grunts]
All that fluff must
be really heavy.
[SHEEP baas]
This coming year is
gonna be all about you.
You should try and look
your best for the occasion.
[SHEEP baas]
I'm kinda jealous!
If I had wool as
wonderful as you've got,
I would be showing it off!
I'd strut my fluff
so everyone could see!
[SHEEP]
Baa!
What? So I can shear you now?
[TOMOE gasps]
[NANAMI laughs]
You're incredible, Nanami!
[NANAMI]
I know, right?
[MIZUKI]
Yup! Incredible!
[TOMOE] Seeing her handle
this with such maturity
makes me miss the child
of twelve years ago.
[TOMOE] I feel so much loss.
Yet, also pride.
You have my gratitude,
land god. I thank you.
[TOMOE]
How did it get so small?
[YEAR GOD]
Here is next year's Talisman.
[NANAMI Oh, thank you
very much, Lord Year God!
[YEAR GOD]
One more thing,
a present. My way
of saying thanks.
I heard you say that after the
fire, you didn't have any left.
But with the memories I saw
while you were in
the Torii Gates of Twelve,
I can make you a print.
What is wrong?
Are you all right?
It's my mom.
[TOMOE]
I see.
They have not
vanished after all.
[TOMOE] Neither the child,
nor the mother.
[TOMOE] Even the emotions
she felt back then.
All of these things
live on inside Nanami.
Even if she may not remember,
she still carries them with her.
[NANAMI]
Oh! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Please take these ones, too!
[SANITATION WORKER]
Sure thing.
[NANAMI sighs]
[NANAMI] It's the first New Year
since I became a god.
So much has happened.
It's hard to believe.
But I'm getting the hang of it.
The talismans for
the first shrine visits
of the year are done!
Perhaps I'm better at this than
I've been giving
myself credit for!
That is just like you, Nanami,
always so thoughtful.
[NANAMI laughs]
[TOMOE]
Let me see.
Ah! Whadja do that for?
Because any worshiper who
is sorry enough to ask your
blessing should not be further
punished by having to read
your orange-scented
chicken scratches!
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI]
The more I think about it,
the more I realize how
much we've gone through.
[OKUNINUSHI]
Yes, yes.
I know, Grandmother Izanami.
But I am extremely
busy preparing
for the new year right now.
Yes, I have made
the arrangements.
For the last time, I promise you
there will be no doughnuts!
[GUARD RABBIT]
Lord Okuninushi,
please look over
these forms as well.
[HIMEMIKO]
I was thinking,
would thou like to
celebrate New Year's?
We could visit
the Mikage Shrine.
[KOTARO]
That's where your friend,
miss Momozono works, right?
Yes, and a day trip
would be so romantic!
[HIMEMIKO] We could start making
our wedding arrangements!
[KOTARO gasps]
Himemiko, I did it!
I set a new personal record!
Kota! Next year for sure.
Next year for sure!
[HIMEMIKO] We will finally
pledge our lives to one another!
[AOTAKE crying]
[KURAMA]
I thought I told you!
Don't book any work for me until
after the twentieth this month!
[KURAMA]
Mm?
[SUIRO]
My, my!
Doors in the Mundane
World are flimsy.
Master Shinjuro!
Brothers and Botanmaru,
what brings you here?
It's been so long
since I've seen you!
I'm, uh, glad to see
you're doing okay.
We have come at the request
of Sojobo the Third.
He sends a resolution.
You are to spend the
new year in training,
and refrain from all further
immersion in the mundane world.
As your senior, I have come
to oversee your progress.
[KURAMA]
What?
Now, that is not our
only reason for coming.
We were concerned for
our brother with whom,
by fate, we have been reunited.
Thus we come as representatives
of the mountain
to make sure you are well.
[KURAMA]
Uh.
Also, we thought you
might take us to the shrine
of the Lady Land God who
has done so much for us.
[KURAMA]
Oh.
That explains why Jiro
wanted to tag along.
[NANAMI]
With the year being over,
I can't help but wonder.
What do we have in
store for us next?
[NANAMI]
The time flew by so fast.
We've laughed, and we've cried.
[NANAMI] It's been crazy,
that's for sure.
[NANAMI]
But it's also been a lot of fun.
[NEWSCASTER]
Hello!
[KOTETSU]
Another year comes to an end.
[ONIKIRI] It feels like
last year had just begun.
[NANAMI]
I know.
Hey! You guys,
it started snowing!
[NANAMI]
Mm?
[NEWSCASTER]
Happy New Year, everyone!
[NANAMI]
Wow, you're right!
Look, it's already
piling up! Cool!
[TOMOE]
Only for the time being.
[NANAMI gasps]
[TOMOE] In a few years,
when you are older,
you will become the
head of a household
more rowdy than you can imagine.
[MIZUKI, ONIKIRI, MAMORU,
KOTETSU shouting]
[NANAMI]
Strange.
I can't remember
who told me that.
[MAMORU]
Nanami?
[NANAMI]
Uh?
[MAMORU]
Can you peel this for me?
I can't get it right.
Sure! No problem.
[MAMORU groans]
You can do that yourself,
you stinking brat!
That's right!
Nanami's not your mom,
so stop acting like a baby!
Calm down.
I don't really mind if Mamoru
thinks of me as his mom for now.
Say "ah."
[MAMORU]
Ah!
Aw. No fair.
Um, Nanami.
You're not planning to
leave us to get married
or anything like that, right?
I want you to stay our
lady and mistress forever,
until you're old and gray and
no man could ever love you!
[NANAMI]
I don't think I like that idea.
Well, I plan on staying
single for a long time.
Or not.
Or not?
[TOMOE chuckles]