Was that another earthquake...?
There have been a lot
of those lately.
Who's there?!
Beware, I am Mitsuko Kongo
of Tokiwadai Middle Scho...
I heard there was another
earthquake yesterday...
Was your dorm
damaged at all?
No, we were fine...
Fortunately my place didn't
really shake that much.
Hmm... That's strange,
considering you're in
District Seven, and all.
Mr. Daigo...
Can I ask you....
why I'm here?
Oh, of course.
Come on in.
A new transfer
student is joining us.
I thought you two
should meet...
since she's going
to be your roommate.
I know it's late notice.
But as our school's
Judgment officer,
we thought you'd be a good
choice to help her get settled.
Oh...! Yes...!
I'll do my best!
Thank you!
I'm Erii Haru'ue.
[Music]
A transfer student
from District Nineteen?
That's odd...
In the middle of
the term like this?
Yeah, usually
transfer students
join at the start
of the year,
or at least the
beginning of a term...
What's gotten
into you, Saten?
You seem really
happy about this.
Well, of course I am!
She's going to be Uiharu's
roommate, after all...
That means she'll
be my friend, too.
Hey, Saten!
So, um...
I'd like you to
meet Erii Haru'ue...
And Haru'ue, these
are my friends.
On the right is
Kuroko Shirai...
Next to her is
Mikoto Misaka.
They both go to Tokiwadai
Middle School...
And that's Ruiko Saten.
She's in our class.
Hello, there...
Uh... if you don't
mind me asking...
Why's all your stuff
just sitting out here?
Oh, yeah...
You see...
I was at the train
station picking up Haru'ue
when we got the call that
the movers were already here
with all of her things.
It wasn't very
considerate of the movers
to just drop
these here and go.
Well, we can't leave
it all sitting here.
I can take care of
that simply enough.
Oh...! Why didn't
I think of that?
Amazing.
I've never seen
teleporting before.
That doesn't
surprise me a bit...
Not to sound immodest,
but there aren't
many teleporters
with my level of power,
even within Academy City.
Okay, okay...!
Now... shall we get
this all put away?
-Yeah!
That's the last
of it, huh?
Thank you all...
I really appreciate
you helping me.
It's no big deal, really...
So anyway...
we finished sooner
than expected...
Let's have some fun, huh?
Agreed!
Don't get too
excited, Uiharu...
Geez, have you already
forgotten...?
We have that joint
conference to attend today.
What conference?
Judgment and Antiskill are
meeting this afternoon.
Supposedly...
it has to do with
all the earthquakes
we've been experiencing
recently.
A conference
on earthquakes?
Yeah. We have to go.
Well... Misaka and I can
still show Haru'ue around.
Without me?
No fair!
It'll be fine.
They can meet up
with us later...
Right?
It'll be okay...
Saten can be a bit too
much to handle sometimes,
but Misaka's nice...
and we'll join you as
soon as we're finished.
Too much to handle?
Saten, I want you to
promise me something...
Swear you won't flip
up Haru'ue's skirt,
even as a joke, okay?
Huh?... But why would I
do something like that?
Well, uh...
you...
you know...
All right...!
Where should we go now?
Your choice...
Anything special
you want to do?
Oh, well, um...
I don't know this district
well enough to say.
Oh... of course.
Hey... I know!
This spot's becoming the
place where friendships begin!
It is, huh...?
This is where we came when
I first met you and Uiharu.
It's good?
You've got a little bit
on your face, though.
Still... it's too bad the
others couldn't come...
Why would Judgment and Antiskill
be holding a joint conference
about something
like earthquakes?
It'd make more sense
if it was a case.
Heh, heh... I didn't really
want to get into it earlier...
but there's a hot rumor
going around about that.
There is one thing
we know for certain
about the recent spate
of tremors in the city.
Despite what many
people think...
they are not earthquakes.
To be precise...
-Poltergeists?
-You're kidding me.
No...! I really
think this is true!
What are we talking
about here...?
Furniture moving around
on its own, and stuff?
No P--waves or S--waves
were observed...!
It's a paranormal phenomenon,
I'm telling you...! Paranormal!
No doubt the rumor mill
is already churning
with all sorts
of absurd ideas,
so let me make this
perfectly clear.
This is not a
paranormal phenomenon.
The cause of poltergeisting
is simultaneous, multiple
incidents of RSPK Syndrome.
What does she mean?
What is RSPK Syndrom?
We're about to find out.
At this point, I am going
to turn the floor over to
Miss Terrestina of the
Multi-Active Rescue Team.
Who'll explain further.
Hello! As Miss Yomikawa
has informed you.
My name is Terrestina
and I am with the
Multi-Active Rescue Team
RSPK Syndrome refers to the
state or phenomenon that occurs
when an esper temporarily
loses their autonomy,
and causing their abilities
to unconsciously
run out of control.
The phenomenon varies
according to the esper.
Please look at the
display if you will.
When these phenomena
occur simultaneously,
the runaway abilities can
merge with each other,
and manifest as a uniform
poltergeist phenomenon.
As the poltergeisting
gains in strength
and spreads over a wide area,
the resulting occurrence can be
virtually indistinguishable
from the effects
of an earthquake.
The recent tremors
we've experienced
are the result of
this poltergeisting.
We're still investigating
the cause of the multiple
RSPK Syndrome incidents
that are responsible.
Unfortunately, there are
sure to be a few students
who will believe this is
some sort of occult power.
It's a pulse from an
alternate dimension!
Or another planet...!
Oh! Or maybe the result of
secret underground experiments
conducted by the government!
In any case...
Belief in such nonsense
could lead to mass hysteria...
which would only increase
the number of casualties.
That is why we
have asked Judgment
to attend this conference...
We want you to take
measures to ensure
that students are not
spreading inflammatory rumors.
Try to put a stop to
them before they start.
They say we can expect
a really big one
to happen before
much longer.
You see?
Oh, yeah, you're from District
Nineteen, right, Haru'ue?
Weren't there several
poltergeisting outbreaks
in that area?
What was it like?
Hey, you shouldn't be
getting so excited
about this kind of thing.
It could be
really serious.
Well, that was over a lot
sooner than I expected.
It says that Antiskill
has an additional meeting
after the joint one.
You look like you have
something on your mind, Konori.
Those RSPK Syndrome incidents
she was describing...
I've never heard of them...
And the way they're
handling this...
something about it just
doesn't sit right with me.
Why? They have specialists
investigating the occurrences.
That's their job,
after all...
At any rate, it's not
gonna do any good for us
to try and figure
it all out.
You're probably right,
but even so...
Hey...! We're done here!
Where are you guys now?
All right, Haru'ue.
What game would you like
to try out next...?
Oh...! I know, over here!
Uiharu sure is in
rare form, huh?
It looks like you are,
too, Sissy
Oh, no... No, these are...
You know, something about those
coins looks familiar to me...
Oh... You're playing
whack--a--mole?
Yeah... Well, sort of anyway.
I played that when
I was younger.
It's so fun.
I've never seen
anything like it before.
Look at them popping
up like that.
So cute!
Yes... very cute...
But, you know...
You might try hitting them,
instead of just staring.
Hit the moles?
But that's cruel.
Oh... I guess you're right.
Uh... okay...!
You can play the game
any way you want to.
One more time.
Um... that'll be the
fourth time in a row...
Hey... you guys,
why don't we check that out?
What is it?
Say "cheese!"
Cheese!
Let's see...
Sending...
There we go!
Here.
How should I put this?
The girl is a curiosity.
Really...?
She seems sweet.
Actually, she reminds me
of how Uiharu used to be.
What do you mean?
You know... back when
she'd first transferred in.
Where are you going?
Look out!
Oh, dear...
You ran right into it.
You okay?
Up there.
That poster?
The one for the
fireworks show?
Oh... yeah, that's supposed
to be tonight, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Hey, we should
all go together.
That's a great idea!
We can dress up
and everything!
Well, what do you say?
-This is gonna be great!
-That sounds awesome!
Yeah!
I never worn one of these.
It feels strange.
Me too, I know
what you mean.
Isn't it a little long?
I'm looking up
how to wear them.
Oh, here, I think
I found something!
Use the sash to
adjust the length...
Sounds easy enough.
It looks pretty complicated.
Well... we can
give it a try!
Let's see here...
First, we pair up
the front, like so...
Ah... What a beautiful pendant!
It's special...
It's kind of a
good luck charm.
A good luck charm, huh?
How nice.
Now... let's see if we
can get this to fit right.
Okay... so what's the
next step in the process?
"After you pair
up the front,
you should raise
the garment's collar
approximately twenty
centimeters..."
I wanted to thank you.
Huh?
I mean it...
You've helped
me so much...
I can tell that
you're a good person.
Oh... it's nothing...
As a Judgment officer,
I'm happy to help you...
Really, I'm having a
lot more fun with this
than with my other
duties lately...
Sweeping up, looking for
stuff people have lost...
Oh, I see.
Anyway... I'm happy
to do anything I can
to help you feel at home...
So... you can
always count on me!
Oh... I'm starting
to understand
why you needed me to
come over so urgently.
Don't just stand there...!
Help us out of this thing!
There!
That should do it.
It's perfect.
Thank you.
That was amazing, Saten...
You made it look perfect
in no time at all!
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
We're gonna be late.
Let's hurry up.
I made a mess of things.
If I'd known how good
you were at this,
I would've asked
before we started.
Come on now,
you're doing just fine.
Well, I figure it should be
my turn to help out this time.
How so?
Do you remember how
difficult it was for me
to pass all those
Judgment tests...
and how that, in turn,
made me insecure
about other stuff, too?
Yeah, I do...
You were in quite
a state, huh?
Constantly getting
down on yourself.
But fortunately, I didn't
have to do it all alone.
You kept encouraging me.
You and the others were there
for me when I needed help.
Oh, yeah...?
And we were helpful?
Yes.
It was all thanks
to you guys.
I finally passed
the tests...!
And that's why...
I think it's my turn now...
to help Haru'ue
the same way that
you guys helped me.
Oh... I mean...
it's not that I'm the only
one you should turn to...
I'm really glad that I have
you for a roommate, Uiharu.
I trust you!
Oh... good!
Look at you...!
Being recognized for your
good deeds at last...
I am so proud!
Geez! You make it sound
as though I'm a little
kid or something.
-My kid sister!
-I'm older than you!
Now, stop fidgeting.
We need to get you
dressed, don't we?
Ready? Let's go.
Whew!
Surely we're safe after
that, don't you think?
Escape successful!
We're on our way!
Could our dorm be
any more of a drag?
They won't even change our
curfew for a fireworks show?
Quit fidgeting. Your outfit will
be down around your ankles
if you continue.
Yeah, okay.
Although... I guess it
doesn't really matter,
since you're still wearing
those stupid shorts under it.
What's the big deal...?
Nobody is gonna see them.
I don't have to see them, but
that doesn't change the fact
that I know you
have them on.
Anyway... Is Konori
coming with us tonight?
Well, she said she wanted
to start investigating
these poltergeisting
incidents...
Something's been
nagging at her
ever since the conference
this afternoon.
Hmm... You have to admit,
it is weird...
All these events occurring,
almost as if they've
been coordinated.
Man, this is
taking me forever.
I don't know if the net's
ever seemed more full
of useless information.
Wow! Misaka,
you look fantastic!
You, too, Shirai.
You're both adorable!
Would you expect any less?
And you guys look
wonderful, as well.
Uh... thank you...
We did try.
Ah! All those stands!
You're right!
There sure are a lot.
Mmm, it smells so good!
-I'm going!
-Me too!
Sissy, be careful
running down that hill!
What do you think...?
Should we go?
Yes, please!
Come on, Sissy.
You look ridiculous.
Hey,... What's the big deal?
It's a festival, right...?
I'm just getting
into the spirit.
Honestly!
Huh? What are
those trucks for?
MAR-They're with the
Multi Active Rescue Team.
They must be a
countermeasure
for all the poltergeisting.
Poltergeisting?!
Then... all the
rumors are true?
It would be a real mess
if one of those
incidents happened here
with all these
people around.
It's not that I don't
get why they're here...
but it's a shame on a
night like tonight...
They don't exactly
blend in at a festival.
Oh...! Just a second.
I know the perfect
place to go!
Nice, huh...?
We've got a great view here.
Hey, look, you guys!
There's another
round going.
You can kind of feel the
"boom" in your tummy,
can't you?
Yeah...
Like... like an echo.
It's so pretty.
Maybe I should have
gone to the festival.
It still feels like
something's wrong.
But I'm not making
any headway.
What's this?
AIM diffusion fields?
What a great show!
Woo--hoo!
Here they come!
-Light up the sky!!
Is something the matter?
I was just remembering.
Remembering what?
More like "who."
You see...
I had a friend once...
We were super close, just
like the two of you are.
Are you okay?
Something wrong?
Where's she going?
Haru'ue!
Hold on a sec!
Huh? I wonder
where they're going.
Finally! They're
taking the hint
and giving us time
alone together!
Now we can imitate
the fireworks
and let our bodies glow
with passionate fire!
Let go...! I don't
feel like fighting you.
It's too hot out here!
As hot as the flame that
burns in my heart for you!
Huh...? Who could it be?
Hi, Konori. What are you doing,
calling me at this hour?
Listen! It's about the
poltergeist incidents!
I know that doing
research is important,
but would it hurt you to take a
breather once in a while...?
The fireworks
show is beautiful.
Just listen to me,
will you?!
I've found a possible cause
for the RSPK Syndrome activity.
Intentional outside
interference
with AIM diffusion fields.
AIM diffusion fields.
So, what are you saying?
That all of this
poltergeisting lately
isn't just some
random accident!
Where are you...?
Where have you gone?
Haru'ue.... what's wrong?
Where are you?
You're saying there's
actually somebody
orchestrating
these events?
What was that...?
Shirai, hello?
Is this...?!
I think so.
It's poltergeisting!
I've got you!
What about the
other three?
Uiharu!
Saten, are you all right?
That was a close call.
Are you injured...?
You're safe now.
I know that lady!
Haru'ue...!
Can you hear me?
Good, you're awake...
Are you okay?
That was quite a fall.
Where...?
Where are you...?
Please, where?
I don't understand.
Wow, that's amazing!
Something's collapsed.
Was there an accident?
[Music]
Where are you?
Where did you go?
This direction, Haru'ue...
No! No...! Not that way...!
Over here!
It's the blind
leading the blind.