That was an odd noise.
What was that? A firecracker?
-It startled me.
-Yeah.
There was another
incident?
Yes, it was the
fifth one so far.
Luckily the explosion
was relatively small,
and no one was hurt.
Even so ...
Even so, if
it's just a prank,
it's not a very funny one.
So, have any leads so far?
Well, it's not much,
but we finally got
something to go on yesterday.
Tell me, Sissy, do you
know about gravitons at all?
Gravitons.
Um, those are gravity
particles, right?
Yes, that's right.
In each of the attacks,
the satellite detected
a sharp spike in gravitons
immediately before
the explosion occurred.
The speed of the
gravitons was accelerated
explosively using
an aluminum base,
so they popped out into
the surrounding area.
Thus, the aluminum was
transformed into a bomb
as far as we can tell.
Hm.
Why use aluminum, though?
-Who knows?
-Well, shouldn't you?
Anyway, at least
this indicates
it was the work of an
Esper, doesn't it?
Just search through
Academy City's databank,
and you should
have the guy.
The data bank registers all of
the students' ability info.
Of course. That was the
first place we turned to.
The corresponding ability
is called Synchrotron.
We found only one Esper
whose power could be used
to make aluminum explode.
It was a Level 4 student.
That's simple. This person
must be the suspect.
Except the thing is,
she has an alibi.
It's solid, too.
The girl has been
in the hospital.
So, there's no way she
could have orchestrated
any of the attacks.
So, that's ruled out.
The inquiry's reached
a dead--end, then?
I'd say so.
I can't believe there
would be such an oversight
in the databank.
Oh. Well, maybe ...
Maybe there's an
unregistered Esper out there
or something.
Hm ...
So, I think I should join in on
the search for this criminal.
No, absolutely not.
I know how you think.
Let's see.
"This could be fun,
facing a new opponent.
Yes, I'd like the chance
to pit my powers against his.
That's exactly what you were
just thinking, wasn't it?
-Don't lie.
-No. I would never think that.
Don't you know that
you can't fool me?
I can see right
through you.
Come on, now.
It's like I've told
you over and over.
Remember that you're
a civilian, Sissy,
and maintaining the peace
of the city---- "...
is a job for Judgment or
Antiskill, and nobody else."
I know.
You've told me
that enough.
If you think I
serve in Judgment
because I get a kick out
of this sort of thing,
you're sadly mistaken.
Now, look. That's not
what I was saying!
Listen to me.
I need you to make
some promises now.
First one, that you will
not go recklessly
poking your nose
into this case.
Is this really necessary?
I don't think
that you're----
And second, in the
unlikely event
that you do become involved,
you will not charge
into a fight,
but wait for Judgment
to arrive on the scene.
Hey, now. I always take care of
things before you guys show----
And third, you must not wear
shorts under your skirt.
What's that got to
do with anything?
It may not deal directly
with this issue,
but I wanted to use
this opportunity
to help you elevate
your sense of style.
You must remember, Sissy,
that as the Ace of Tokiwadai,
you have
an image to uphold.
You still seem to lack the
self awareness necessary
This is totally off--topic!
No. Please listen to me.
If you were more self--aware,
you would realize that the
Ace should not sleep
with a teddy bear nor bathe
with a strange frog doll.
It's about time for you to let
go of those childish things.
And there's more.
For instance, those cutesy
pajamas you insist on wearing.
I mean, you are the third
ranked Level 5 Esper
Who do you think you are?
Why should I ever
listen to you?
Oh. I see.
Well, what do you think?
Uh, well, maybe ...
Could you sit down,
if that's okay?
I think it'll help.
Here's my theory.
I think Shirai means well
and her concern is keeping
you safe and out of danger.
Out of danger?
Like with these graviton
attacks we've had.
Oh. Is that their
formal name now?
At first, they were just
put into empty tin cans
or garbage bins, but the
suspect has evolved.
The latest bombs were put
into stuffed animals
or other toys to make
them less suspicious.
Who would do that? It's awful.
You can see how
serious it is now
and why Shirai might be a bit
concerned about you helping.
Thank you for waiting.
One fruit parfait,
as ordered.
Wow! Finally!
I am so hungry!
U--i--ha--ru!
Oh! Hello, Shirai.
Trying to duck your
responsibility
by lounging around here?
Well? Are you ready
to go on patrol?
Of course.
Oh! But, uh, my parfait.
Uh ... Aw, just a bite? Please?
I asked Uiharu to join
me here to have a snack.
Hm?
If that's a problem, then
you should talk to me.
It's nothing
to do with you.
This is exclusively
a Judgment matter.
So, we civilians should
butt out, is that it?
What more do you
want from me, Sissy?
Like I've already
explained,
whatever you want to imagine,
Judgment work isn't exactly
a walk in the park.
Wha-?
Ah, my parfait!
Please, just one bite!
She is so condescending!
All I hear is "Judgment
this" and "Judgment that."
I'd be more impressed by
them if they showed up
before I'd taken
care of everything.
Well, whatever.
I'll give it to her later.
What are you just
standing around for?
Uh, sorry.
You mean me?
Do I have it wrong?
Are you not my backup?
Your backup? What?
Oh! No.
You see, funny story, one
of my friends just left this
Stop blabbering
and put on your armband.
We need to go!
Come with me.
What? Where are we going?
To do our jobs, obviously.
Oh. Have you not heard yet?
To do our jobs?
That means I----
Hey. You don't know what's
going on, do you?
Come to think of it, I
don't know your face.
Are you one of
the new recruits?
Hm ...
Yes! I'm Misaka,
and this is my
first day!
Misaka.
You know, I think I've
heard that somewhere before.
I'm sorry, but I
don't know your name.
I'm Mii Konori of
the 177th Branch.
Good afternoon, Konori.
Nice to meet you!
Oh. Yes. Same to you.
I'll show her that a
civilian is perfectly
capable of doing
Judgment work.
They can throw whatever
they want at me.
I'll take it!
Here.
What is that thing?
What is this? It's a broom,
obviously.
Oh.
We're here to tidy
this place up.
Uh, really?
It's just, well, you know.
I'm in Judgment and all.
Exactly. Students throw
their litter about,
and we in Judgment have
to pick up after them.
Didn't you learn that
in your training?
Eh-Oh!
Yes, I remember that now!
This is what
Judgment does?
You've got to
be kidding me.
Hey, you just threw
trash on the ground!
Oh. You can get this, too.
You little punk!
Come back here, right now!
Huh. You got
what you deserved.
Now throw
-Eh---- Huh? Uh ...
Seriously?
I can't believe anybody
would be careless enough
to leave their
armband here.
Well, what did they say?
No luck.
No one saw anything
matching its description,
and nothing's
been turned in.
I'm sorry.
What am I going
to do with you?
You'll have to submit
an official report.
But, for now, let's go
back to the branch office a-
What's the matter?
Are you lost, sweetie?
What were you thinking?
You can't get
trigger--happy with your powers.
Yeah, but ...
"But" nothing Misaka.
The use of your
ability is one thing.
Guarding the safety of
the city is another.
Uh ... Oh, yeah.
I think I remember now.
That was part
of my training.
Before you look
to your training,
look to your common sense.
The work of Judgment isn't
exactly a walk in the park!
Come on.
I'll do better!
I promise you I
can do this job!
Yes, of course.
Just hang in there.
It's no use.
I should quit.
Oh, thank you.
Being out in the field is a
lot different than training,
isn't it?
Yeah. Totally.
I guess I never realized
how difficult it could be
to give directions
and help people.
Yeah. It was
hard for me, too.
You know, the maps.
It can be a hassle
even when you think
you know the place.
Yes. Konori here.
Right.
I hear you.
We'll both keep our
eyes open for it, then.
Well, it looks like we've
got something to find.
Oh yeah, really?
Yeah. They say it's a bag.
A bag?
In the beginning it
was just garbage bins,
but the latest bombs were
put into stuffed animals
or other toys to make
them less suspicious.
The bag we want, could it
be a kid's by any chance?
Well, yeah, but how
did you know that?
Apparently it's pink and
has some flowers on it.
She said she
left it on a bench,
and then a dog grabbed it
and started running away.
No! Not a dog!
We have to do
something now!
Come on. Let's hurry
up and go catch it.
Well, yeah.
It would be a pain if
he dropped it somewhere.
You're worried about that?
We would have no way of
telling who walked away with it,
so ... It
could be anywhere.
Let's go!
We need to find that bag!
Uh ... Uh--huh.
Of course.
Hey, sorry.
But I can't really
squeeze through there.
Don't worry about it.
I'm almost all the
way through. I think.
Are you okay, Misaka?
There's a bug.
It has lots of legs.
Ah! No! Get away!
Aw, come on.
Where are you hiding?
What is it?
There's a bug. It has no legs!
Ah! No! Get away!
Hm.
No, nothing here.
Why do I have to
be on the bottom?
And what is she doing?
The bag we're looking for
isn't gonna be up there.
This is stupid!
A little bit more to
the right, please.
Yeah. Sure.
Ah! There's a bug!
Ah! Whoa. Steady, now.
Oh, really? Area D, as well?
Okay, thank you.
We appreciate all your
help with this matter.
Oh, hey. Is Uiharu here?
Yeah, she's in the back.
Yes. Judgment. Branch 177.
There you are!
You gotta listen to this.
I finally found the
song I was looking for.
Shh!
She's finally tired
enough to sleep.
Aw, she's adorable!
I never knew you
had a little girl.
Yeah! No. Wait.
So, when will
she get flowers?
You know these don't grow
out of my head, right?
Oh, I see.
And for your information,
I don't have any
children, either.
But look at her.
Right around the eyes.
Do you see?
Not my daughter!
Easy, now.
You'll wake her up if
you're not careful.
You're the one
being loud, Saten.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
So, who is she?
Did she get lost
or something?
It's not that.
We're just trying to help
find her bag for her,
that's all.
Apparently it was a birthday
present from her parents,
so it's very important.
So we've asked the other
branches to assist us
in the search, also.
Until the search
is complete,
Shirai and I are
looking after her.
Wow. All of Judgment
looking for a bag?
Why is it such a big deal?
Life is much
different here.
You're completely separated
from your family.
It's something
everybody understands
when a child is homesick.
Hm. Judgment handles more than
I ever realized before now.
There, there.
It really matters.
I'm sick of this.
Where are you?
Hey! Watch where
you're going, punk.
You bump into someone
without apologizing?
No. I didn't.
You ran----
Aw, look. The little
twerp wants to argue!
Stop it! What are you doing?
It's Judgment.
So no big deal, then.
What do you mean,
"No big deal then"?
You two were just
ganging up on that guy.
Shut up already.
What a brat.
No. Patience. Patience.
Are you okay?
It's a little
late for that.
That wasn't very polite.
Hey, Misaka.
Well? Did you find it?
Oh! No.
Not here either, huh?
Where haven't we looked
for it yet? Let's see.
Maybe here.
No. Please don't tell
me it's in the park.
There are all
these kids here.
True. Children and dogs
don't always get along.
Dogs? That's not what
I'm talking about!
Really?
Because it's a dog
we're looking for.
No, I ... I mean,
are you sure?
Let's concentrate
on the bag.
Why don't you start
over there, okay?
Hey! Don't leave me!
Off you go, now.
That's not fair.
Hey, lady, are you
a Judgment officer?
That's a
Tokiwadai uniform!
Are you a princess?
Uh, I ...
She's wearing shorts
underneath her skirt. Look!
Why do you think
she's wearing those?
Maybe it's a
princess thing.
Hey. Don't you have
underwear like normal people?
I'm wearing them
underneath the shorts!
She's going commando!
A commando
Judgment officer!
You don't know what
you're talking about!
Ooh, look. A dog!
Got you!
Konori, quick!
Stop right there!
I can take care of this.
He's fast! I don't
have any choice.
Hah--hah! I've got you!
Huh?
Look out!
No!
It's mine now!
Misaka!
Target safely recovered.
-She's so cool!
-Totally Tokiwadai!
-She is a princess!
-I knew it.
Well done, Misaka.
That was something.
Whoa! Uh, don't you think you
should handle it more gently?
And shouldn't we be calling
in the bomb squad now?
Uh,
what are you
talking about?
Here. Try not to
lose it again.
Yeah!
That was really good work.
I knew Konori
would come through!
I'm not the one who
found it, actually.
-What are you doing here?
-Oh, it's Misaka!
I'm sorry. I didn't realize
you were acquainted
with Misaka.
Um, acquainted with her?
That's Mikoto Misaka.
You know, from Tokiwadai?
Mikoto. Misaka.
You don't mean
the Railgun?
Well, yeah. But what
is she doing here?
And, more importantly,
what is she doing soaking wet?
Oh, about that.
She actually dove
into the fountain
to protect the
bag from going in.
Apparently
she was convinced
that there was a
bomb inside the bag.
Hey, is that my ... ?
Seriously, how
does this happen
after all the lectures
I've given her?
Hey, now. This is totally
something she would do.
K--Kuroko!
I, uh, I can explain.
There's no need
to be flustered.
Miss Railgun of Tokiwadai.
Oh. Uh, well ...
She knows, then?
Okay, that's cool.
Come on. This way.
Pretty lady.
Thanks a lot!
Oh.
I mean, really I just ...
You're very welcome!
-Good job, sweetie.
-Mm--hm!
After everything
I said, Sissy,
Job well done.
This has been one heck
of a day, hasn't it?
You'll get no
sympathy from me.
You're the one who decided
to play Judgment officer
because you were
annoyed with the rules
I'd laid out for you.
I hope you learned your
lesson this time, at least.
It sure is hard, huh?
Being in Judgment, I mean.
What are you saying?
Maybe I should look at
you in a different light.
You don't know how
much I have longed
for this day to come.
Please look at me in
a different light!
If this one doesn't work,
I'm happy to change
it for you, Sissy!
Whoa! No! I didn't mean
that literally!
Sissy!
Sissy! Just look at me!
I'll change the light!
Anything you want!
Oh, Sissy!
Keep it down!
We're with Judgment!
I need everybody to
evacuate the store at once!
Hey, what's going on?
What's happening
in my store?
Sir, we have detected
accelerated gravitons here.
You what?
I'm sorry, but it's
possible there's a bomb
hidden somewhere
in this store.
Wha? A bomb?
Damn. Where is it?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I fell.
Let's get you out of here.
Thank you.
No! Not yet!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
He shielded me.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
I said I was gonna do
it, and I'm doing it now!
Doing what? Who are you?