Bye!
I'll miss you so much!
I'm so sorry, Erii.
But don't worry...
We'll see
each other again.
-Bye!
-See you later!
See you!
Bye, Banri!
Take care of yourself.
[Music]
That's how Banri and I met.
We were in the same
Child Error facility.
I'm really shy
around other people,
so I don't make
friends easily.
But for some reason,
it wasn't as hard to
be friends with Banri.
Whenever she spoke to me,
it was always using
our telepathy.
but then she was transferred
to another facility.
And that was it.
But lately...
I've been hearing
Banri's voice again...
just like when
we were young.
She's asking for help...
telling me she's
in a lot of pain.
But I... I don't know why...
and I have no idea
where she is now.
I want to help her.
But there's
nothing I can do.
I wish... I wish I
knew where she was.
It will be all right!
I'm sure you'll
find her again.
No... I'll find her for you!
As a Judgment officer,
that's the least
that I can do.
You really can?
Yeah! Despite her appearance,
Uiharu's actually an
excellent Judgment officer.
"Despite my appearance?"
Oh, sorry...
my bad.
Anyway, just leave
it to me, okay?
Thank you so much!
You must be tired
after all this.
You should get some rest.
No. I'm fine, really.
The Level Upper incident.
-You mean...?
-Yes.
Harumi Kiyama
was responsible,
and I saw into her past.
Haru'ue's friend, Edasaki,
was in the flashback.
An induced burst experiment
to analyze the law
of runaway abilities.
It's hard to believe such an
experiment would be conducted.
I know. From what I can tell,
the person in
charge of it all
was an old researcher
named Kihara.
Kihara...? Do you
mean Gensei Kihara?
I've never heard of him.
He's a scientist...
A famous one,
in some respects.
Though "mad scientist"
might be more accurate.
I know some of his work.
He's not above human
experimentation.
His current whereabouts
are unknown, however.
If he actually carried
out such an experiment...
then it's entirely possible
that the children he used
are the source of the
recent poltergeisting.
What do you mean exactly?
That all those
child subjects
have become runaway espers.
How's that possible.
Kiyama was certain the
children are asleep, even now.
What if their abilities
are out of control
while they're unconscious?
Oh, no.
You think the interference
isn't intentional,
but rather the accidental result
of their unconscious state?
It is a possibility.
Where are the children now,
do you girls know?
Antiskill has been searching for
them ever since the incident,
but they still haven't
discovered their location.
Oh.
Well, it sounds like
finding these kids
is our top priority.
Now then, the lucky
color of the day is pink.
That's a good sign, huh?
Whoa... this is crazy!
You're telling me that
Edasaki, Haru'ue's friend,
was one of Kiyama's
students...
and that these
children are the ones
causing the poltergeisting?
Yes, that's the
hypothesis, anyway.
Until we actually
locate the children,
we can't know anything
for certain, though.
Okay, but how are we
supposed to find them?
Well, maybe...
I see what you're
getting at.
We should use the computer
to find where they are.
That means you're
up, Uiharu!
Right...? You'll look.
Of course I'm
going to look...
but I don't like this.
We've cleared Haru'ue,
and now you turn around
and start suspecting
her friend?
That's it!
You're being unreasonable!
Those poor kids.
They need help.
They're pleading.
Hey, Sissy?
You've been in there
for a long time.
Yeah.
I've got a lot to think about.
After today,
I guess we all have.
So what are you
going to do?
Don't you want to
make up with Uiharu?
It's not like I don't
understand why she's upset.
But still...
I'm a Judgment officer.
I've done nothing more
than duty requires.
Uiharu feels betrayed because
I investigated her friend.
Even so...
I'm sure she'll
come around.
She'll see that I just...
Don't think I'm gonna
let you come in here
just because we're talking!
Huh?... I thought it would be
a perfect opportunity for...
Get out!
Here. I brought snacks.
They're from a shop
in District Eight
that's famous
for its pastries.
You went that
far to get them?
You'll understand why.
These are the best cakes
in all of Academy City.
Oh, I got the
sweet--bean filling.
You have to go
with the classic.
Wow...
That far and
they're still warm?
Actually...
That's because I used
my ability on them.
It doesn't sound
that fancy,
but I can maintain the
temperature of things I touch.
I can't handle anything
that's really hot,
so I just stick with
moderately warm items,
like pastry.
I haven't told the
others about this...
not even Saten.
But it's only fair.
You told me about
your ability,
so I told you about mine!
So... it's good?
It's delicious.
It's so good.
According to
Kiyama's deposition,
there were ten human
experimentation subjects.
They were all put in
a vegetative state.
And then they
were divided up
and taken to different treatment
centers across the city.
But they aren't
there anymore?
Right. They were
transferred repeatedly,
and somewhere along the way,
the trail vanishes.
Yeah.
How about you take
a quick break?
No, thank you.
Saten... where are you going?
Uh... I don't know.
Well... why don't
we get a drink?
Thanks. It's just really hard
to be around
them right now.
I know.
I wish there wasn't so
much tension between them.
We need to find
Edasaki somehow.
For Haru'ue's
sake naturally...
but for Uiharu's
sake as well...
and I'm sure it would
make us feel better also.
Absolutely.
Who's that...?
Yes, Misaka here?
-Kiyama is out on bail?!
-Yes.
I went to speak with her
at the detention center
about the child experiments,
but she'd been released.
After everything she did,
I can't believe they would
let her see the light of day!
I don't know the specifics
of her bail agreement...
but it's a done deal.
Crazy!
I don't know how
we'll ever be able
to locate the
children without her.
Huh...
Something about this
doesn't make sense.
Everything Kiyama did was
for the sole purpose
of rescuing those children.
Why would she go
through all that
just to turn around and
use them like this?
It's not so surprising.
She is the same one who
exploited students' desires
to increase their abilities.
I said no, thanks.
How about you stop
playing the martyr?
Oh. I'm sorry.
You've been at
this for a while.
I'm surprised you haven't been
able to track them down yet.
I'm not done.
There's still more data
that I need to trace.
Hey... what's this, here?
It's something about AIM
Diffusion--field resonance.
And how that's a
possible cause
for mass outbreaks
of RSPK syndrome.
Resonance?
Yes, that's right.
The way in which the
AIM diffusion fields
of similarly--typed espers
resonate with each other.
It starts with one runaway
esper being tampered with.
Then, like a domino effect,
other espers of a like type
are triggered as well.
The resonating esper powers
share general characteristics.
Let's look at your
ability as an example.
Similar types would
include espers
who can manipulate either
electrical or magnetic fields.
Which means there is a
wide range of espers
who could resonate with you.
And that means... A
similarly wide range exists
for the ten child experiments
who have gone missing.
Imagine if all of their
runaway abilities
have been activated.
Their sphere of influence among
other students would be huge.
As high as
seventy--eight percent.
Really...?
Seventy--eight...?!
But then.
We could see poltergeisting
on such a large scale
that it would tear
apart the entire city.
All right, but who says
this theory is correct?
Take a closer look at the
person who wrote this article.
Gensei Kihara?
After what we
learned earlier,
I looked into him.
His whereabouts are
indeed unknown,
just as Therestina told us.
All of the research facilities
he was associated with
are shut down...
and his data has
been scattered.
What is it?
Is something the matter?
Huh...? Oh, no.
Not really.
Ah! Oh, Sissy!
Oh, you're so rough!
No, please don't stop!
If I had time,
I'd slap her silly
and put a stop to
whatever she's dreaming.
I'm sorry.
All right.
My disguise is complete.
If the power isn't on,
I guess I didn't need a mask.
I was right.
This is it.
For whatever good that does.
No, there is
nothing left here.
Yes. I'm pulling out now.
It's her!
You again.
I knew it.
Harumi Kiyama.
Can I help you
with something?
Are you responsible for
these latest events, too?
What would you
do if I was?
Stop you, that's what!
Hey...! What the...
What's happening?
Well, that's that.
Nice job back there...
Sending an
electric current
through a dead
security system.
It's not like that's
what I meant to happen.
But never mind that...
What were you
doing there?
How did you get
out on bail?
What are you
planning now?
This situation feels
regrettably familiar to me.
Being interrogated in my
own car by a schoolgirl.
-Huh?
-Well, sorry.
But the questions will
have to wait for later.
What is this place?
Come this way.
What's that?
If you've peeked
through my memories,
you should know the
answer to that question.
These are them.
These are my students.
I was right.
You are the one
who's behind all these
poltergeisting incidents.
I am.
It's true.
However, there is a rather
long story behind it all.
Oh, and... as you
may have noticed,
this is a hospital.
Please try to refrain from
the use of electric shocks.
I remember you!
Long time, no see, huh?
Will someone please tell
me what's going on here?
Gensei Kihara.
It was with him that
all of this first began.
Consider these questions.
Why are we here?
What is our
ultimate purpose?
For what reason was Academy City
designed and built
in the first place?
Yes... there is one
fundamental reason.
Creating a being who
transcends mankind:
A Level Six.
What you are
looking at now
are the results
of much research.
Signal pathways form
that differ from a
normal neural network
within the brains
of runaway espers.
Various neurotransmitters
and hormones
are secreted abnormally.
Through the process of
extracting those secretions
and then condensing
and refining them,
we can produce an ability
crystal such as this.
And by administering
this crystal
to a specially--selected esper,
we can produce the long
sought after Level Six.
Yes, the ability crystal
will help us realize the
ultimate purpose of our city.
The creation of SYSTEM.
After all these years of
stumbling through the dark
we may at last find someone
who attains the power of God
while still inhabiting
a mortal body.
You really believe it?
That you'll be able
to create a Level Six
using your ability crystal.
Of course I believe it.
And the price?
Intentionally impairing
consciousness...
leaving the subjects vulnerable
to serious side effects.
My experiments have
produced consistent results.
Is that so?
And how many
victims do you have?
Victims?
My research produces
answers, not victims.
Don't be ridiculous.
Perhaps he truly
did not see the harm
he was causing
with his work.
But there were victims.
The more I learned about
the facts of the case,
the more convinced I became.
Finally, there
was no denying it.
The Child Errors that Kiyama was
trying so desperately to save
were used as test subjects
for Kihara's ability crystal.
The burst experiment
I told you about.
The one that analyzed
runaway abilities...
that was part of it, too.
The experiment you
saw in my memory
was a dosing of the
ability crystals.
Crazy... all this to
create a Level Six,
which we barely
know anything about?
These poor kids have
ended up like this.
And that's the
reason behind it?!
And now I am
doing what I can.
I hope my talents
as a doctor
will allow me to save them.
Luckily, it didn't
take too much time
to get them all
transferred into my care.
My name carries a
certain amount of weight
in this town, you see.
However, I did need to
speak to a specialist
about how to revive them.
That's how you made bail.
He did me a great favor.
I'll be forever grateful.
Thanks to my access
to this facility,
I have a rough idea of how
to revive the children.
You can save them?
Unfortunately, another
problem has arisen.
What's that?
As they approach
awakening...
their AIM diffusion field
readings have abnormal values.
Which means?
Their powers are
out of control.
They've triggered cases of
multiple simultaneous
RSPK Syndrome.
But why?
It seems Kihara's research
hasn't stopped entirely.
If he was using the
ability crystal
that I knew he
had developed,
then the children
should not have set off
any poltergeisting events.
But there seems to be an
upgraded crystal at work here.
He has turned these
children into runaway espers.
Even as they lie here,
in a deep sleep.
So... if you did
try to wake them up,
the poltergeisting.
Yes.
The force would
be incalculable.
What now?
We have to do something.
I am developing a program
that will bring their abilities
under control, but...
The building block of
Kihara's ability crystal
is known as the
First Sample...
It is a refined extraction
that is derived from the
very first human subject
of the experiment.
If I'm going to complete
the vaccine software,
I have to analyze the data
contained within that sample.
So then that's why you were
back at that laboratory.
Yes, I was looking
for that data.
Unfortunately, I
didn't find anything.
But I'm not
about to give up.
That data is indispensible
to the continued research
of ability crystals.
There's no way something
like that would be discarded.
It must be out
there somewhere...
and I swear,
I'll do whatever it
takes to find it!
I see.
And what if you can't?
Then I will still
wake up the children.
Even knowing the kind
of damage it'll cause?!
I will not allow them to
remain like this forever!
I understand...
but... you can't.
She's right.
Because I won't let you.
Therestina?
Hello, there.
Sorry, but I followed you.
What the...?
We're the Multi
Active Rescue Team.
These children are
in our custody.
It's best if you
do as we instruct.
Do I have a choice
in the matter?
No. It's our duty to
seek out and prevent
any situation that might
endanger Academy City.
Naturally, I have a
warrant with me.
Feel free to read it...
though, I had hoped
you would cooperate
and make the
process easier.
This looks to be in order.
Please, don't worry.
This kind of thing
is our specialty.
We have a facility ready
to offer the children
whatever treatment
they need.
But, please...
And our data access
exceeds yours.
We can find information you
could never lawfully obtain.
Earlier, you mentioned something
called the First Sample.
It's possible that
we can acquire data
on that item as well.
Secure them.
Hold on!
What are you doing?
You told me that if I didn't
like what you were doing,
I'd have to come
and stop you.
Move, now! I'm the only one
who can possibly
save those children!
But you haven't, have you? !
First it was the
Level Upper...
now these poltergeist
attacks... and still...
You haven't saved
one of them.
I'm so close, though.
I'm just one step away.
I have to.
You know Edasaki?
Well, she's asking
for help, even now.
I met this girl.
Her name is Haru'ue.
She's Edasaki's friend.
She can hear her voice.
[Music]
Carry them out.
I'm nervous. It's been a while
since I've done a preview.
I'll feel more comfortable if
I just remove some clothing...
For the millionth time: No...!
Things are getting serious,
so behave!