Kuroko!
Use of your abilities inside
the dorms is prohibited...
How many times do
I have to say it?
Right... Misaka?
[Music]
Give me a break.
What an old bat...
All she ever talks
about is rules!
Well, that is kind of her
job description, you know.
Is there nothing we can do
to make her chill out
a little bit...?
I was just teasing
you yesterday;
it's not like I was
doing any harm to anyone.
Why am I always the
one she chooses
to vent her frustration on...?
I'm telling you,
she's a bitter old maid.
I wouldn't let her
hear you say that.
That's the truth of the
situation, though, isn't it?
She's the head resident
of a girls' dormitory,
a job that offers zero
contact with men.
No wonder she's
still single.
But she shouldn't
take it out on us;
it isn't our fault
she's heartless and alone.
That was just her,
wasn't it?
Yeah, but what
is she up to?
There's something
off here.
She's dressed like
a normal person.
Now that you mention it,
I've noticed that
she goes out somewhere
whenever she has time off.
To meet a man! Huh?
Come on. This is the
perfect opportunity!
Kuroko, where
are you going?
So... do you have
a plan, here?
Oh, yes. We're
going to follow her
and get leverage
to use against her.
Leverage? Like what?
It must be a blind date...
I can't imagine that somebody
would willingly go out
with such an inhuman harpy
after actually meeting her.
Although, whoever set her up
must be quite a gambler.
What are the chances
of this matchmaking
foray turning out well...?
Oh! Perhaps her
date lost a bet
and has to go out
with her as payment.
I think that's taking
it a little far.
Odd place for a blind date.
I see now.
Her mystery man
must be Italian...
An Italian man
named Marco!
Okay, now you're
just making stuff up.
School District 13...
All this way...?
What on earth is
she doing here?
How long do you plan
to follow her, anyway?
Until I get to see her darling
Marco with my own eyes.
Yes, of course. "Marco."
Ah... hey look, Auntie's here!
Best be careful who you're
calling Auntie, young man...
If you want some
of this yummy food,
you should call
me Big Sister.
Wow!... It's pizza!
Now, now, there's
no need to push.
I brought enough
for everybody.
No way.
This is Asunaro Park
Children's Orphanage...
It says here that this is
a Child Error facility.
Huh...? That's the
term they use for kids
who are left in Academy
City without any family.
As always, thanks
so much for coming.
It's nothing.
The little ones always look
forward to seeing you...
"When's Big Sister coming?"
they ask.
I'm sure I enjoy it
more than they do.
The help you give
us is priceless...
I can't tell you
how much we appreciate
having you volunteer here.
I hope you'll continue
coming for a long time.
Yes, I will.
Big Sister, you're gonna
eat with us, aren't you?
Just try to stop me.
I've never seen her
act like this before...
She's so... happy.
This is unusual indeed...
I never would have guessed
that this is what she'd
choose to do on her days off.
To think I had no idea
that the noble Head Resident
had such a tender
heart buried
underneath her
rough exterior.
"Noble"?
Compared to her, we
are selfish children...
I am ashamed to think of all
the horrible things we said...
calling her a
bitter old harpy...!
Idiots...!
Uh, you're the one
who said all that...
Hold on...
It's not fair for them to
make us do community service
because we had
lousy test scores.
This could be a valuable
life experience.
Besides, it's fun playing
with the children
and seeing their
smiling faces.
Yeah... I guess you're
right about that.
Oh... excuse me...
do you have a moment?
I want to introduce
you to our director...
Saten, Uiharu, this is
Miss Kazuko Shigenomori.
It's a pleasure
to meet you...
Are these two girls
students of yours, Daigo?
They are.
I want to thank you in advance
for all your help today.
Not at all.
We're happy to be here.
By the way...
are those two over there
friends of yours by any chance?
Huh?
What a coincidence running
into you guys here, huh?
Are you guys
volunteering, too?
Oh... um... y'see...
Hey... isn't that the head
resident of your dorm in there?
Did the three of
you come together?
Oh, no... Certain
circumstances led us here,
but I won't go into it.
Okay... nicely done, everybody.
Hello!
It's nice to
see you again.
Oh... it's nice
to see you, too.
A couple of my students
came to volunteer today...
They're new, so they might
make some mistakes...
Please feel free to
tell them if they do.
Oh, no, no...
I'm sure that none
of your charges
could do anything wrong...
Don't be silly...
Plus... I don't
have much experience
when it comes to
scolding students.
Wow... I had no idea your head
resident volunteered here.
Maybe Mr. Daigo
asked her to help out.
The man she's talking to
in there is called Mr. Daigo?
Yes, that's his name.
He's our homeroom teacher.
Finally, her mystery man
has been revealed to us.
Huh?... What are
you talking about?
Isn't it obvious?
Our head resident has fallen
head over heels
in love with him!
-Wha-?
-In love?!
I have a mission.
I will see to it that her
love does not go unrequited...
I will not fail her!
I don't know about
this, Kuroko...
I do...! I think it
could be a lot of fun.
I'll help, too.
She deserves a happy ending!
You guys're getting on
board with this idea, too...?
I hope you realize it's not
going to be a simple task.
Fortunately, Shirai
has a devious talent
for creating
romantic situations.
How about I give you
a smack on the head?
It's no good to ask
after you've done it...
That wasn't nice.
Okay, that's enough
standing around...
Let's hold a
strategy meeting!
Oh, noble head resident...
We welcome you home.
What do you think
you're doing?
You do not care for
a moist towel...?
Then please allow me to
take your bag for you.
Oh, look at that...
I see you've chosen a higher
end beverage than normal...
Did something
special happen today?
What kind of joke
are you playing?
I don't mind
punishing you again.
No joke, ma'am.
Helping you in your time
of need is my only desire.
If you have anything you
need to get off your chest,
you can confide in me.
Anything at all!
Discuss my personal
life with you...?
No way, not a chance...
Don't be absurd.
Forgive me...
I only want to be of service
to my noble role model.
I can tell when you're up
to something, Shirai...
What is it?
I'm not up to
anything at all...
I'm sorry I've given
you reason to think so.
It's just that today
I had the chance
to see you playing with
the poor young orphans,
and I gained so much
respect for you!
How do you know
about that?
That's not even
the half of it.
I know about
Mr. aigo, too...
Right...? We know it all?
Oh, uh... well...
Uh--huh!
All right, you! What exactly
do you know about Daigo?
Won't you let us help you
this once, Head Resident?
Help how?
We could play the part of
Cupid for you and Mr. Daigo.
Wouldn't that be great?
No...! Never...! Why
would I need Cupid?
Besides... I'm not even
interested in Mr. Daigo.
Ma'am surely you do
not want to deny
the true desires
of your heart.
That would be tragic!
You may as well admit that
what you want from Mr. Daigo
goes beyond friendship...
It's no use
saying otherwise.
I can see right
through you.
Why you little, what gives
you the right to say that?
It's been twenty--nine
long years.
Hasn't the time come to
know the joys of love?
Isn't that what
you deserve?
Just... go away!
Are you sure you want to
spend the rest of your life
as an old maid?
K--Kuroko...!
If you let this
chance pass you by,
you may not get
another one...
I have my own experience
with unrequited love.
Please, Head Resident,
allow me to help you make
your dreams come true!
Er... don't you think
that's enough...?
Eh?
You mean it?
This isn't just some trick?
You really wanna help me?
Yes. I really do.
Eh...
Huh?!
These lovely girls
have volunteered
to play with you
this afternoon...
Let's give them a nice,
warm welcome, okay?
It's nice to
meet all of you.
What a great turnout...
I'm so glad your students
could come along ...
You must be really
proud of them
for volunteering like this.
Oh... yes...
I'm very proud.
-Mr. Daigo!
-Yes?
What is it?
So... what's this brilliant plan
for me, Shirai...? What now?
You just relax and
take it easy for now...
Your love life is in very
capable hands, I can assure you.
All right. We're going to
put the plan into action
immediately.
So there is a plan?
Oh... well...
Mission accomplished! I've got
her all settled in the kitchen.
Good. Excellent work, Saten...
With that done,
phase one of the plan
is officially complete.
On to phase two.
In which we get
the head resident
and Mr. Daigo alone together.
Having them participate in
a collaborative activity
is a surefire way to
bring them closer...
Our plan needs a name...
"Operation Fruits of Love"
is now in effect.
"Fruits of Love?"
Are you sure...?
Doesn't that make
it sound improper?
Well... the fruits of love
are children, aren't they?
Hey, Big Sisters...
Come play with us!
Well, you heard
the girl, Sissy...
Why don't you go
and play with them?
You remember us discussing
this part, don't you?
Oh... well, okay then.
All right, everyone!
Let's go!
Oh, Shirai... what am I...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Daigo, hi...
Why are you-?
Well...
I wanted to come help
you with the cake.
I have to admit,
I'm really impressed
that you're going to
make a cake from scratch
for the birthday party...
Homemade is always better.
Well... uh...
Well, how about I get
started on the icing?
I know I don't look it,
but I am fairly
good at cooking...
or I try.
There's something about
baking a cake from scratch
that feels so homey.
Oh... Yeah...
It may sound silly...
but this is the kind
of thing I love.
It's so fulfilling...
the act of
creating something.
Sorry, I realize
I'm blabbering...
but this is so nice.
It's just-I'm hoping to
get married someday...
and standing in the kitchen
like this with my wife
is a favorite
daydream of mine.
I wonder how they're
getting along so far.
Come to think of it,
we just assumed
that things were going to
go well between them...
What do we do if it
doesn't go as we planned?
Well, you see...
Hey, that sounded like the
head resident, didn't it?
-What in the world?
-Calm down.
There's nothing
to worry about...
Naturally, I made sure to
prepare contingency plans
should anything
unexpected happen.
Ah...! What's going on?
It looks like
something exploded!
What is all this?
Uh. I can explain.
It was all my fault...
I was trying to open a bag
of flour, and it just...
All of this from
opening a bag of flour?
Hey... It'll be okay...
We can start over...
No problem... Right?
Right... thank you, Daigo.
Unfortunately, there
isn't enough time for that
before the
birthday party.
So... maybe you
could run out
and get us a
replacement cake.
Oh... I guess you're
right... Okay...
If you could wait one sec.
Our noble head resident
here knows of a cake shop
that should
work perfectly!
Sh... Shirai!
It's fine.
Don't be nervous...
These two will go along
with you for moral support.
You're coming?
Yes...!
We're at your service.
Hurry! Run away!
This is crazy.
What am I doing here?
Hah...! I caught you!
Yeah... I was no
match for you...
and I guess that means
it's my turn to be "it."
Now... run...
Run as fast as you can,
or I'm gonna catch you!
I would do anything
to save them...
anything in the
entire world!
The whole city can
hate and revile me.
I don't care!
I'm not going to let
anything stop me now!
Child Errors...
Huh...
-"Happy Birthday Meg &amp; Kei"
-Happy Birthday, Meg and Kei!!
Hip, hip, hooray!
It ended up being
a big ordeal.
First we went
the wrong way...
Then we got
chased by a dog...
And nearly fell
into the river.
How could that happen?
You were just
buying a cake.
Well... who cares?
It turned out all
right in the end.
All right, everybody...
Time to dig in!
Yeah!
This is nice, huh...?
Everybody's having
such a good time.
I'm sorry...
I... I wish I could've
been more helpful today.
Oh, hey...
I haven't seen you
without your glasses...
It looks nice.
Oh... I mean... you look
good with them on, too...
but you also look pretty
when you take them off.
Look at that! They're being all
lovey--dovey with each other!
Hah! Lovey--dovey!
Hey...! You shouldn't be
teasing grownups like that!
That's just silly...
For one thing, I'm certain
that your Big Sister
would have no interest
in me whatsoever.
I've got an idea.
How about you describe your
ideal woman for us, Mr. Daigo?
Huh... well, let me see....
Someone I could respect,
I guess.
Someone you can
respect, huh?
And what would
that require?
Well... she would really
have to be somebody
who puts the needs of others
before her own, you know?
Earthquake?!
Right... okay...
everybody stay...
Listen up! Everybody take
cover under the table.
Good... now stay
there and keep qui...
Be careful!
Has it stopped?
We've had a lot
of these lately...
Thankfully it was small...
We'll be fine.
Oh, no!
Miss! Are you two okay?
Young man...! Didn't I tell
everyone to get under the table?
Yes... I'm sorry, Big Sister.
It'll be okay. Are you
sure you're not hurt?
Oh, wow.
You were fantastic.
You have my respect.
No, really...
it was nothing.
You were fantastic.
You have my respect.
-No, really...
-And so...
I would like to marry you.
Say yes, and we'll
cook together forever.
Yes.
I am so sorry.
I know I was
out past curfew.
These things happen...
Just try to be more
punctual next time.
That's unbelievable...
I've never seen
the head resident
overlook a curfew
infraction before.
It was inevitable,
I suppose.
Love changes a person.
Yes, hello...?
Oh...! Daigo!
Huh...? There's something
you wanna ask me...?
And you're sure
you want me...?
It has to be me, you say...?
All right.
I'll be there.
What does he need to
ask her so urgently?
Isn't it obvious?
After today, there's only
one thing it could possibly be.
Huh?
He's going to propose?
I can't believe it's
really happening!
This is so exciting,
I can hardly stand it!
Why would he choose a
family restaurant like this?
It is pretty pathetic...
I'm guessing he's never
had a girlfriend before
so he doesn't have
any idea what to do.
Obviously when a man
proposes to a woman,
it should be at sunset
in a fancy, romantic
restaurant on the beach!
No... a rooftop restaurant
with a view of the city...
Right... Misaka?
Yes, and then...
after she's accepted
his gallant proposal...
they climb on
top of a mountain
and watch a fireworks display!
-That's going a little far.
What?
So, anyway...
You said there's something
you wanted to ask me...
Yes... I guess I should just
come right out and say it.
Yes?
I was wondering...
How would you feel
about marrying somebody
who is younger than you?
M--Marrying...
Someone... younger?
Yes... for instance...
someone like me.
I've got you now!
Well... I, uh...
I don't really
think age matters...
not as long as you
respect the person.
I knew it...!
I figured you
would say that,
but I just wanted
to make sure.
Sorry for calling
you out of the blue
to ask you
something like that.
No...
Congratulations!
Way to go!
You mean you
were watching?
Head Resident, I knew
you had it in you...!
Now, you'll need
to pick a venue...
and meet his parents...
And then honeymoon!
Shirai... I would appreciate it
if you would give me a
hard pinch on the cheek.
Huh?
If this is all
just a dream,
I'd like to wake up now.
Well if you insist.
Okay. That's enough, Shirai.
Before you go...
There's one additional
favor I need to ask of you.
I, uh...
I want to give him
a proper answer.
Around and around and
around and around......
Hello, Daigo...
Around and around and
around and around......
Do you... have a sec?
I can't put my
finger on it,
but there's something
different about you today.
Um... about our conversation
the other night...
Yes. I really
appreciated that...
I finally have
the courage I need,
and it's all thanks to you.
Oh! What's this?
I'm going to propose
to my girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
That's right.
And your girlfriend is...
Yes...
I was nervous.
But then you said
age doesn't matter
as long as you
respect the person...
and I knew you were right.
I can't tell you how
grateful I am to you.
Sure.
It's no problem...
I'm glad I could help.
Congratulations...
I wish you all the best.
All right.
Aww... I was sure it was
going to work out for her.
That's a shame.
I bet she'll find
someone else before long.
Of course she will.
She's a great person.
Okay, everyone...!
What are we going
to play today?
[Music]
No fair! I couldn't've been
more than a second late!
It doesn't matter if
it's an hour, a second,
or a tenth of a second.
Whatever the case,
you broke curfew.
I hope you're prepared to
answer for that, Shirai.
Kuroko!
Kuroko!!
Now, Head Resident,
I know you've suffered
a major disappointment,
but don't let it
get you down...
Just think of
those children
looking up at you with their
sweet, angelic faces...
Mow them down!