Time to get out
of bed, Sissy...
The day has finally come!
Aren't you excited?
No, not exactly.
But it's your
moment to shine!
I know big,
important events
are pretty much an everyday
occurrence for you,
but today is extra special...
I'm not the only
one who thinks so...
The rest of the girls in
our dorm have been waiting
for this almost as
anxiously as I have.
My moment to shine, huh?
There must have been
any number of girls
who would've been
better suited
for something like
this than I am.
Aw... always modest...!
You shouldn't be.
If you ask a hundred people
who best represents
the pride of Tokiwadai,
every single one of them
would say your name.
Well... since it's all set,
it's too late
to back out now.
That's the attitude
I'm looking for...
Now, then...
Let's see about getting
you changed, shall we?
I can dress myself.
I don't need your help.
Let's get this over with.
[Music]
One day out of each year, the
Tokiwadai Girls' dormitories
open their doors
to the public...
This is a special
annual event.
It's our midsummer festival.
You have all invited
special guests,
and today they will
be allowed inside.
I expect you all
to behave in a way
that befits your status
as Tokiwadai dorm residents.
There will be no missteps!
I get that we want
to be hospitable...
but are these outfits
really necessary?
Welcome to our dorm...
Would you like a pamphlet
listing today's events?
You sure are cute...
Can I take a picture?
I'm afraid not, sorry...
We ask that within the
dorms there be no photography.
Yeah...! Work it...!
Work it!
No photography!
Yes!... Yes...! Yes...
Perfect!
What did I just say...?
Why are you taking pictures?
I am working in an
official capacity...
I'm the midsummer festival's
archivist this year.
Somebody needs
to take pictures...
Future classes will want to
look back on this festival.
But Sissy...
I have to say,
your outfit doesn't
photograph well
with those stupid
shorts underneath it...
Couldn't you put on something a
little nicer for the occasion?
Please tell me, Kuroko...
How exactly will sticking
a camera up my skirt
help future Tokiwadai classes
to "look back" on this
year's festival...? Huh?!
Now, now, Sissy.
I think we have a
misunderstanding here...
Hey, you guys!
You two are
always wrestling.
I can't thank you enough
for inviting us, Shirai...
What an honor...!
We're here for the exclusive
Tokiwadai Middle School
midsummer festival!
I can't wait...!
I'm certain
today's festivities
will exceed even my
wildest imaginations!
I'm glad you
could be here...
We won't disappoint...
The events to come
will be memorable...
I'm certain you'll enjoy
everything we have to offer.
Now then... shall I take
you on a little tour?
Just a minute.
Shirai... when were you
planning on helping us out
with the buffet?
Uh... I, uh, guess
I must have forgotten.
So...?
Oh, allow me to
introduce you...
This is Maika Tsuchimikado,
from Ryouran Girls'
Housekeeping School...
She and her classmates are
helping us out this year...
They're overseeing all
the food for the festival.
Oh, I've heard
of that place!
They really specialize in
training future housekeepers?
Yes, they do.
It's a pleasure
to meet you.
Maika... These are two
very good friends of mine...
Kazari Uiharu and...
Ruiko Saten.
Hey, there.
It's so nice to meet you!
If there's
anything you need,
feel free to
give me a shout.
And as for you...
time to work!
Hey...! Stop dragging me
for a second, will you...?
I can't just
abandon my friends.
Oh, but you can abandon
your work, is that it?
Now you're just
twisting my words.
I can show you around,
since she's busy.
All right, then...
What should we start
with first...?
Is there anywhere
you'd like to...
Yes!...
Yes, yes, yes!
There is someplace I'd
like to see, very much!
Right here...
and here... and here...
Oh...! And from here
to down there, too.
Okay... everywhere, then?
I'll have you know...
For today, at least,
I am no longer mild--mannered
Kazari Uiharu...!
Yes, I hereby announce...
The arrival of my alter ego!
Well... that's fine...
We'll see everything
there is to see.
Wow!... What an
incredible display...!
That's what you get from
a top--notch school...
Well...? What
do you think?
Are all of these really
made entirely of sugar...?
It seems almost
impossible.
Let's see...
Yep, that's pure
sugar all right.
You can't just eat
that, you know...!
They're handcrafted
display models...!
Right... Misaka...?
Here, Misaka.
Have another, please.
It's really no trouble at all.
Oh... thanks...
It's lovely, really,
but I don't think so.
Wow... the detailing
on this is amazing.
Oh, hey, look at that!
We can even do
it ourselves!
Okay, Uiharu...
I'll give it a try.
You're going to come with us,
aren't you, Misaka?
Oh, well...
Thank you, but...
That settles it!
This'll be great...
Okay we've got a
party of three.
I think I did a
pretty decent job...
Here, take a look, Saten.
This one's not quite as
good as the one I made
for my brother's book--bag.
Oh, hey...
how's it coming?
Oh, wow...! These
are magnificent!
You can really tell that
these were arranged by
proper young ladies, huh?
They're all so
graceful and refined.
I think that's exactly the
impression they want to give...
This is a girls'
school, after all.
Excuse me, I
was wondering...
Did you arrange all the
flowers here by yourselves?
Yes, that's why we're
displaying them.
Oh...! They're
very beautiful.
Thanks for saying so...
We tried.
I have to say, the
flowers in your hair
are far prettier
than these are.
It's true.
You have an eye for
arrangements, clearly.
What are you talking about?
Tokiwadai is a fine
institution...
The festival is perfect.
I'm amazed...
Each exhibit is flawless...
Our school could never
aspire to this...
Tokiwadai has achieved
a greatness
that few places
could hope to match.
Well, Saten...?
Don't you agree?
You're awful! How could
you do that to me,
here of all places?!
Welcome back.
Well... you were
looking so dreamy,
I had to wake you up.
I wasn't dreaming,
thank you very much.
I'm wide awake!
Here. That should do it.
Thank you so very much...!
Oh... and please allow me to
wish you the very best of luck.
Yeah, well... thanks...
That's nice of you.
Lucky...! I can't believe
Misaka tied your apron for you.
Just look at her, Uiharu...
She's what Tokiwadai
is all about.
Yeah... that is so true.
So... are you guys
getting hungry?
That's it, I don't
ever want to leave!
I'm just going to have
to move in with you.
I'll go look for
a seat, all right?
Oh... okay.
What's wrong...?
Oh, is it not cut yet?
Well. Allow me.
How could you do that to
such an exquisite cake?!
This from someone who
didn't think twice about
popping a sugar
statue in her mouth?
How can you possibly
eat that much cake?
People always say you
have a second stomach
for desserts, right?
I... I can't move...
That's what happens when you
eat twenty plates of food.
But... it's good...
and they said it was
all you can eat...
Come on...
we can't let the students
see you in this state...
Move it...
Get up, get up!
If you're not careful,
it's all gonna come back up!
Big Sister Mikoto!
Huh...?
You're from Asunaro Park...
So, what are
you doing here?
I invited them
to come today.
Guess what?
We made rings out of
beads and drew pictures
and built stuff with sugar!
Wow... that sounds like fun.
Yeah, it was...!
But you want to know what
I'm most excited about...?
-Do you?
-Yes...
I would love to know.
Seeing Big Sister
Mikoto on stage!
Me, too.
I can't wait!
Yeah, I hope it's not
gonna be much longer!
Okay, wait. Who told
you guys about that...?
It's not a big deal, really!
Yeah...! We're gonna
cheer for you...!
Good luck, Big Sister!
You heard her, right...?
You're going to give
them a show to remember.
Yes... Of course.
Now, now...
No running.
You might fall
and get hurt.
I mean...
Absolutely no running!
That's just great...
Does she think putting
extra pressure on me
is gonna make me
do any better?
Hey, Misaka!
Are you really gonna
perform something for us?
Huh?...
Oh, well, I...
Yeah...! Really...?
So how come you didn't say
anything about it earlier...?
Oh...! I get it!
It's gonna be a surprise!
Huh?...
No, no, no...
It isn't like that.
Don't worry about it...
We won't ask any
more questions.
But... Ah...! Quiet...!
Say no more...!
We'll just wait and see.
Yeah, don't tell us...
I want it to be
a surprise...
Ah... what could it be?
I can't wait to find out!
Um... yeah...
Hey, Misaka!
Have you seen Shirai
around lately?
Didn't you
take her earlier
to help you out
with the buffet?
Yeah, but she's not in
the kitchen anymore...
The little brat must
have run away on me.
One of the guests here is
a freakishly big eater,
so we have our hands full
just getting enough
food on the table.
It's a big hassle.
Kuroko... she's so sneaky.
Oh, yeah...
Good luck today.
I can't wait to
see you up there!
So much suspense...!
Oh, my!
It's killing me!
Ah! That was one
delicious meal!
What's up next?
Where to?
Well, isn't it obvious?
No... Where?
Well, if we keep going
straight, we can...
Uh, sorry, guys.
I need to use the
restroom real quick...
Go on ahead without me.
Hey... what's up with her...?
She's been acting kinda
nervous and twitchy.
Really? You think so?
Last call, everybody.
Do we have any
other bidders?
Saten, look...
Something's going
on out here.
I don't hear anybody...
Okay...! That makes
this our final bid!
Oh, that's cool...
They're having an auction.
Those are some incredibly
rare items up for bid...
I've seen some of that
stuff in a magazine.
It's so exclusive, you can't
even get it on the market.
Leave it to Tokiwadai!
Hey there, Konori!
Oh... what are
you doing here?
I had no idea you were
into purses that much.
Oh...! No... this isn't
my style normally.
They're doing it for
charity, though...
The proceeds they get from the
auction are being donated
to the Child
Error children...
As a member of Judgment,
it is expected for
me to participate.
You know...
that sounds suspiciously
like an excuse.
Well... it isn't.
Well, why don't you
guys bid on something?
No...
I don't think we can...
We can't afford it.
We don't have a whole
lot of spending money.
Oh, that's all right.
Let's see what we have now.
It's a lovely
stationery set.
We'll start the
bidding at one hundred!
200! 300! 400!
There, you see?
I guess you're right...
Okay. 10,000!
Why are you here...?
Tsuchimikado's been
looking all over for you.
This is the reason you abandoned
your duty in the kitchen...?
Just to drop a bunch of
money on some stationery?
Oh, no...
This isn't just a stationery
set, I'll have you know.
It is so very much more...
You see, it was put
up for auction
by none other than Sissy...
These pens and pencils...
these pages...
They are a part of her,
like bits of her soul.
I... am so... lucky!
Those belonged
to Misaka...
That explains it.
Speaking of which,
where is she...?
She's not with you?
Oh... well, you see...
Good afternoon, ladies.
Just perfect.
What are you doing here...?
And what's with that
outfit you've got on?
I should think that
would be obvious,
even to someone like you.
I felt certain you
would need coaching
on what it is to
be a proper maid,
so I condescended
to come and provide
the benefit of my
expert instruction...
I know...! I am so
generous of spirit.
So benevolent!
I cordially invite you
to study my impeccably
attired self...
This maid uniform is
authentically English...
With an Eastern flair,
of course...
It was designed
specifically for today.
There's nothing authentic
about that get--up.
All right then, Shirai...
Let's test your skill...
I want you to say,
"Welcome home, my lady."
Oh yeah?!
Why would I want to do
something like that?
You can't do it,
can you...?
Poor dear, even
with that outfit,
I can see you're hopeless.
I humbly beg your pardon...
I wonder if you would
be kind enough
to offer a demonstration?
I know so very little
about good manners, you see.
Oh, very well...
I am Mitsuko Kongo,
the Maid of Maids.
I will show you
how it is done.
Please, watch
me very closely.
First a little
twirl, and then...
Welcome home, my lady.
-It is so good to see you.
-Yes...
Now, my friends and
I are very thirsty.
Please bring drinks
for everybody.
Yes, of course, my lady.
Right away.
Thank goodness simple--minded
folk are so easy to handle.
Hey, guys.
Good to see you.
Yes, how have you been?
Probably a lot better
than you two ...
having to put up with
someone like her.
She can be
trying sometimes,
but she's not a
bad person, really.
Yeah, she's actually the one
who invited us to the
midsummer festival...
She's spent the whole
year waiting for it...
That's why we're here.
Wait... I'm confused now.
You guys don't all
live here in the dorm?
No, actually
Tokiwadai's girls
are split up between two
different dormitories...
There's this one,
of course,
and then there's also one
inside the Garden of Learning.
Wannai, Kongo, and I all
live in the other one.
You live in the
Garden of Learning...?!
That magical paradise filled
with elegant young ladies?
Anyway... is Misaka
around somewhere?
Come to think of it,
we haven't seen her since
she took a bathroom break.
Oh... That's too bad.
I wanted to tell
her how excited I am
about seeing her
perform today.
Do you know what kind of
performance Misaka's giving?
No, we have no idea.
It's a surprise!
Ooh... I wonder what it is?
Oh! That's right!
This is no time for me to
be hanging around here.
I have to get a good seat
so I can capture Sissy's
performance on camera!
I wish they would
stop being so excited.
Oh, no...
I'm breaking
out in a sweat!
Do I have the jitters...?
No. No way...
That can't be happening
to me of all people.
I wonder what kind of
surprise she has in store
for her performance.
I can't wait to find out.
Oh, dear...
My heart's
starting to pound,
and I've got butterflies
in my stomach!
Why are you nervous?
It's not your show.
You guys are close, Shirai.
Do you know what Misaka's
going to do up there?
Of course I do.
However... my lips
are firmly sealed.
S--E--A--L--E--D!
Lovely!
Look at the flowers!
I can barely walk.
Oh, no...
My heart's going a
million miles an hour.
Ah...! You've got to
get it together, now!
Um... Hey...
Sorry if I'm interrupting...
It's just... I got separated
from the person I came with.
Maybe you've seen
her around...?
She's about this tall,
and she's wearing a nun's habit.
What are you doing here?
I said, what are you doing here?
Answer me!
Whoa... I'm sorry...!
Uh... I'm not doing
anything wrong...
See, I have an invitation
and everything.
Did you come here to
make fun of me...?
You wanted to laugh
at my silly dress?
No... No way...
I think it looks really
pretty, actual...
Get outta here!
What is with that guy?
He chooses now of
all times to show up?
I'm already enough on edge!
Oh, cool. She's
doing a violin solo!
Oh, wow...! I didn't even
know that she could play.
Look at that.
They have no
idea I'm nervous.
All right, then.
What do you know.
It looks like that guy is
good for something, after all...
I didn't see that coming.
[Music]
Hey! Do you feel
that swaying...?
Back and forth...
Now, Sissy,
you know I'm steadfast.
I would never waver in
the face of your lov--
I'm talking about
an earthquake!