- SOUND OFF. FIGHT, FIGHT.
- FIGHT, FIGHT, FIGHT.
- SOUND OFF. FIGHT, FIGHT,
FIGHT. FIGHT, FIGHT, FIGHT.
- SOUND OFF. FIGHT, FIGHT.
- FIGHT, FIGHT, FIGHT.
- ( police siren wailing )
- SOUND OFF. FIGHT, FIGHT.
- FIGHT, FIGHT, FIGHT.
- HOPE YOU'RE READY,
POVERTY GOD.
I'M GONNA TAKE YOU OUT
WITH EVERYTHING I'VE GOT.
I REFUSE TO PUT UP
WITH ANYMORE CRAP.
YOU MUST NOT BE A
VERY OMNIPOTENT GOD
TO THINK YOU COULD
WIN AGAINST ME.
- ( scoffs ) REALLY?
YOU JUST SAID THAT?
HMM. GIRL, YOU CRACK ME UP.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
- OKAY. AS I'M SURE
YOU CAN TELL,
THE TEACHER WHO'S NORMALLY
IN CHARGE OF GIRLS' PHYS ED
IS OUT SICK TODAY.
SO, INSTEAD OF SEPARATING
THE BOYS AND THE GIRLS,
WE'RE GONNA TRY A JOINT CLASS,
AND SEE IF YOU GUYS
CAN HANDLE IT.
WE'LL BE PLAYING
MIXED PAIRS TENNIS.
- HUH?
- DOUBLES, HUH?
I GUESS THAT MEANS I NEED
TO PICK OUT WHAT BOY
I WANT TO BE PAIRED WITH.
- COME ON, AT LEAST TALK TO HIM.
HEY, THERE, HOW'S IT GOING,
BIG FELLA?
- ( sighs ) HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- UH, WOULD YOU LIKE,
I DON'T KNOW,
UM, WOULD YOU MAYBE
WANT TO PAIR UP WITH ME, ER...
- YEAH, SURE.
- ( gasps )
- THAT'S IT, LET HER RIP.
- ( laughs ) OH, BUT I CAN'T.
- HERE, PUT YOUR HIPS INTO IT.
- HOLY CRAP,
FROM THESE DOUBLES WILL SPRING A
LIFETIME OF DOUBLES.
- ( church bell ringing )
- OR AT LEAST THAT MAY HAPPEN.
I MEAN, ONE CAN DREAM,
CAN'T THEY? ONE CAN DREAM!
- SO, ANYONE GOT ANY IDEA
WHAT THAT'S ALL ABOUT?
- MISS SAKURA?
- ( screaming )
- WOULD YOU MIND
PAIRING UP WITH ME?
- NO, CHOOSE ME.
- HE'S A LOSER, CHOOSE ME.
- JUST A MOMENT, BOYS.
- COMMONERS SUCH AS YOURSELVES
ARE UNFIT TO PAIR WITH THE
LOVELY AND NOBLE ICHIKO SAKURA.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU, BRO?
- I'M THE PRINCE
OF THE TENNIS CLUB.
ADENOKOJI. SHION ADENOKOJI.
- YOU'RE NOT A REAL PRINCE.
- YEAH, TENNIS CLUB IS NOT
ROYALTY, DUDE.
- SHE NEEDS SOMEONE
SIMILARLY NOBLE.
SOMEONE SIMILAR
LIKE ME, SPECIFICALLY.
- SO, WOULD YOU CARE
TO PAIR UP WITH MOI?
- All: MOI?
- YEAH, SURE. ANYONE'S FINE.
I'M NOT REALLY ALL
THAT PARTICULAR.
- DID YOU JUST
WIPE YOUR HAND OFF?
- GROSS.
- DO THEY KNOW HOW
RIDICULOUS THEY LOOK?
- YEAH, I DOUBT IT.
THEY'RE BEING RUDE, TOO.
LIKE, WHAT ABOUT US?
- Momiji: QUIT COMPLAINING.
- HUH?
- THE MORE SENSITIVE YOU ARE
TO HOW THEY'RE ACTING,
THE RUDER, THEY'LL BE.
- ( all exclaiming )
- IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
WHY DON'T YOU FOLLOW MY LEAD,
BUCK UP, AND DO SOMETHING
ABOUT IT.
- All: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- SERIOUSLY? YOU BROUGHT
A GORILLA WITH YOU?
- MEET MR. GORIHARA.
HE'S IN TENNIS CLUB WITH ME.
WE'VE BEEN RIVALS EVER SINCE
WE WERE IN MIDDLE SCHOOL.
I'M KNOWN AS THE TECHNICIAN.
AND HE'S THE CRUSHER.
WE'RE PRETTY FAMOUS. I'M SHOCKED
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD OF US.
WE'VE ALREADY HAD
SEVERAL MAJOR...
- WELL, NONE OF THAT
MAKES ANY DIFFERENCE.
- WHAT? YES IT DOES.
- BEAT THAT GIRL AND I'LL GIVE
YOU A YEAR'S SUPPLY OF BANANAS.
- ( roaring )
- LET'S DO THIS!
IF I'M GOING UP AGAINST YOU,
I'M NOT GONNA HOLD BACK.
I'M GONNA TAKE YOU OUT WITH
EVERY SINGLE THING I'VE GOT.
NO MORE OF YOUR CRAP.
YOU MUST NOT BE A
VERY OMNIPOTENT GOD
TO THINK YOU COULD
WIN AGAINST ME.
- REALLY? YOU JUST SAID THAT?
GIRL, YOU CRACK ME UP.
NOW, COME ON. LET'S GO.
- LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE BOTH READY
FOR A FIGHT. GOOD LUCK, GUYS.
- COME TO THINK OF IT, A
REGULAR GAME WOULD BE SO BORING.
SO, INSTEAD, CARE TO
MAKE A LITTLE WAGER?
THAT OUGHTA GET US
REAL FIRED UP.
- THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
WHEN I WIN, WILL YOU FINALLY
DISAPPEAR FROM MY LIFE FOR GOOD?
NOTICE I SAID 'WHEN' NOT 'IF'!
- OKAY, WHATEVER, PRINCESS.
AND IN RETURN, WHEN YOU LOSE,
YOU'LL GIVE ME ALL OF YOUR
HAPPINESS ENERGY, BITCH FREE.
- ( both growling )
- Momiji: YOU LOSERS
WANNA MAKE A BET, TOO?
- SURE, SOUNDS FUN. I'LL WAGER.
- HE'S WILLING TO DO ANYTHING.
IF WE LOSE, HE'LL SHAVE
HALF HIS HAIR OFF,
AND RENAME HIMSELF
THE BALDING PRINCE.
- WHAT?
NUMBER ONE, YOU CAME UP WITH
THAT NIGHTMARE WAY TOO FAST,
AND TWO, YOU COULD
HAVE ASKED ME.
- DON'T UNDERESTIMATE
THE DETERMINATION OF ROYALTY.
- SAYS THE GIRL WHO
UNDERESTIMATES
THE DETERMINATION OF A GORILLA.
- IF WE LOSE, GORIHARA
WILL PUT ON A SHOW
TITLED "SHE-GORILLA IN HEAT".
HE'LL WRITE A BOOK ABOUT
HIS WEEK IN A CAGE
WITH HER AND TITLE IT,
HOW I LOST MY VIRGINITY.
- ( grunts )
- THEREIN LIES A FIGHT
WE CANNOT LOSE.
- ( whistles )
- I HAVEN'T PLAYED TENNIS A TON,
BUT THERE'S STILL NO WAY THE
POVERTY GOD CAN BEAT ME.
I JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE
I DON'T RETURN THE BALL
TO SASQUATCH OVER THERE.
- ( all exclaiming )
- THAT GORILLA KNOWS
HOW TO PLAY FOR REAL.
- BAD APE! LEAVE HER ALONE!
- HOW COULD YOU DO THAT TO HER?
- YOU'RE A MONSTER.
- KNOCK IT OFF. THIS IS TENNIS.
TRY TO BE MORE CIVILIZED.
IF YOU CAN'T UNDERSTAND WHY,
THEN REMOVE YOURSELVES
FROM THIS COURT AT ONCE.
AND BESIDES,
YOU SHOULD BE FAR MORE
CONCERNED ABOUT ICHIKO,
INSTEAD OF FOCUSING USELESS
ANGER AT A HUMAN APE HYBRID.
- PRINCE, THANK YOU.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
ANY HUMILIATION I SUFFER
ON THE COURT,
DESERVES TO BE PAID BACK
ON THE COURT.
- YOU UNDERSTOOD?
AND I WAS BEING SO VAGUE, TOO.
- OKAY, HERE COMES
THE NEXT ONE. SERVICE.
- ( yelling )
- OH, NO. ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT, GORIHARA?
- ( groaning )
- HEY.
- HUH?
- IT'S ONLY GOING TO GET WORSE
FROM HERE, BELIEVE YOU ME.
- NICE. NOT BAD AT ALL, ICHIKO.
- THAT SHOULD BE ENCOURAGING.
IT'S MY TURN.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY.
- I MAY NOT HAVE
GORIHARA'S POWER,
BUT MY SERVE
HAS A TENDENCY TO CHANGE.
YOU CAN TRY TO KEEP UP,
THOUGH I HIGHLY DOUBT YOU CAN.
- ( yells )
- OH, WOW. WAY TO AIM
FOR THE ACE, BRO.
- HUH?
- GUM-GUM STRETCHY ARM.
KING OF THE PIRATES!
- HEY, ISN'T SOMETHING
LIKE STRETCHING YOUR ARMS
AGAINST THE RULES?
- AFTER ALL THIS, ALL YOU
CARE ABOUT IS RULES?
WHAT IS THE DEAL WITH THESE TWO?
- FROM THAT POINT ON, WITH
GORIHARA COWERING AROUND ICHIKO,
AND THE PRINCE BEING BAFFLED
BY MOMIJI'S IMPOSSIBLE MOVES,
THIS MATCH HAS TAKEN,
WHAT I WOULD CALL,
SOME UNEXPECTED TURNS.
AND NOW, WE'RE IN THE FINAL SET.
- ( Shion chuckles ) MOMIJI.
TO BE HONEST, YOUR TRICKY MOVES
THREW ME OFF AT FIRST,
BUT NOW I'M STARTING TO ADAPT
TO HOW ABSURDLY CRAZY THEY ARE.
- SO, YOU THINK YOU HAVE ALL MY
MOVES FIGURED OUT, DO YOU?
WELL, ALLOW ME TO DEMONSTRATE
WHAT TRICKY REALLY LOOKS LIKE.
- ( all exclaiming )
- WHAT KIND OF MOVE IS THAT?
IT'S LIKE THERE'S MORE
THAN ONE MOMIJI OUT THERE!
- ( grunts )
- BY MOVING FAST ENOUGH, SHE'S
MAKING AFTER IMAGES OF HERSELF.
WHAT KIND OF A GIRL IS SHE?
WAIT, CALM DOWN
AND FOCUS, SHION.
DON'T PANIC. THERE'S
ONLY ONE OF HER,
AND THERE'S ONLY ONE BALL.
AND I KNOW WHICH ONE IS REAL.
- ( screaming )
- I DID NOT SEE THAT COMING.
- HECK, YEAH.
- THAT WAS AWESOME.
SHE'S NOT HALF BAD.
- THOSE AREN'T AFTER IMAGES,
THEY'RE NOTHING BUT
CLONES, CHEATING.
OH, PRINCE, TELL ME YOU'RE OKAY!
- I'VE HAD IT, I CAN'T GO ON.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
ANYTHING IS ANYMORE.
- YOU HAVE GOT TO GET
A HOLD OF YOURSELF, PRINCE!
- GO, ICHIKO. IT'S ALL
UP TO YOU, NOW.
SERIOUSLY, DON'T LET...
THEM SHAVE MY HEAD.
- PRINCE, NO!
YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS!
TIME OUT A SECOND.
I'VE GOT TO GET MY RACKET.
- THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
- ( yawning )
- HMM? WAIT, THAT'S NOT JUST ANY
OLD RACKET. WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
IT'S TOTALLY YOUR SOMIN SHORAI.
- ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
- YEAH, HERE WHAT GOES?
- HEY, MORON, WHAT DO
YOU THINK WILL HAPPEN
IF YOU USE THAT IN
FRONT OF EVERYONE?
- ( wind whooshing )
- THAT WIND CAME OUTTA NOWHERE.
- THERE'S SAND IN MY
EYES. I CAN'T SEE.
- MAN, HER DAMN HAPPINESS ENERGY
COMES IN HANDY.
BUT YOU GO TOO FAR.
- Ranmaru: ICHIKO! MOMIJI!
- THIS IS A BATTLE
TO AVENGE THE PRINCE.
- BUT I'M NOT DEAD.
- TAKE THIS, POVERTY GOD!
- LADY LUCK DOESN'T GIVE UP,
DOES SHE? THAT'S FINE BY ME.
SHE'S NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN PLAY THAT GAME.
- Teacher: WHOA!
WHO'S STILL IN THERE?
- Akane: BOOBS, FLAT-CHEST,
THE PRINCE, AND THE GORILLA!
- THANK YOU FOR
MAKING THAT CLEAR.
AT ANY RATE, THE REST
OF YOU TAKE SHELTER.
- ( gasps )
- ( Momiji howling )
- All: I CAN SEE
SOMETHING IN THERE!
- JEEZ. WHAT IN THE HOLY CRAP?
SOMETHING STRANGE IS
GOING ON INSIDE THAT STORM!
- ( both yelling )
- THIS IS NOT HOW
YOU PLAY TENNIS.
- ( both screaming )
- ( yawning )
- PLEASE, CLASS BE OVER ALREADY.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED HERE?
- WELP. SINCE WE CAN'T EXACTLY
USE THE COURTS ANYMORE,
TENNIS IS CANCELLED.
- YEAH, BUT A TIE HERE
IS NOT GONNA CUT IT!
- I DON'T THINK THIS
GAME WILL END
WITHOUT SOMEONE LOSING AN EYE OR
MORE LIKELY DYING.
- MAN, YOU GIRLS ARE
ON FIRE TODAY.
AND SO, WITH THE MATCH BEING
CALLED, THE GAME ENDS IN A TIE.
AND THE PRINCE AND GORILLA
GET OUT OF THEIR PENALTY GAME.
- WE'VE GOT YOUR FAVORITE, SON.
SAKURA-MOCHI!
- WE GOT SOME MOMIJI MANJU
FROM HIROSHIMA FOR YOU.
- I'M SCARED OF MOMIJI.
- Ranmaru: THEY EACH DEVELOPED
A CASE OF GYNOPHOBIA,
WHICH IS A FEAR OF CHICKS,
NOT LADY-DOCTORS.
AND ALL'S WELL THAT ENDS WELL.
- ( together ) NOTHING'S WELL!
- Students: THIS WEEK'S.
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO.
- GUESS WHO'S FINALLY
A CHARACTER, PEOPLE?
I MADE IT, I MADE IT, I REALLY
MADE IT. ( screams )
- YOU'VE MADE YOURSELF CLEAR.
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO GO THAT
FAR, I WILL ALLOW IT.
AT THIS JUNCTURE THEN,
I CHOOSE TO LEAVE EVERYTHING
UP TO YOUR DISCRETION.
FEEL FREE TO OBSERVE
THE SITUATION IN PERSON
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
IF YOU ARE SUCCESSFUL,
YOU WILL MOST CERTAINLY
BE REWARDED FOR YOUR EFFORTS.
- ALL RIGHT, I'VE PUT THIS OFF
FOR LONG ENOUGH.
TODAY IS THE DAY.
I'M GONNA COOK FOR MYSELF
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER.
YAY, ME.
SUWANO SAID,
- OKAY, I JUST NEED TO RELAX.
IF I SET MY MIND TO IT,
I CAN HANDLE COOKING,
NO PROBLEM.
SURE, I'M A BEGINNER AND CAN'T
NECESSARILY MAKE FOOD
THE WAY YOU DO
RIGHT OFF THE BAT, SUWANO.
BUT I DO KNOW THAT IF I CAN
MAKE EVERYONE ELSE THINK
WHAT I COOK IS TASTY,
THAT'S ALL I NEED TO FEEL
LIKE I DID A GOOD JOB.
GAH, WHY DOES TSUWABUKI
ALWAYS SHOW UP IN MY HEAD?
- WHATEVER. I'M FOCUSED
AND I'M GONNA DO THIS.
OKAY, NOW. LOOKS LIKE I NEED
TO TAKE CARE OF THE RICE FIRST.
- IT'S STEAMY IN HERE,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- GET OUT OF MY HOUSE.
- IF I'D WON THAT TENNIS MATCH,
I WOULDN'T HAVE TO LOOK AT HER
UGLY FACE AGAIN.
MY BIGGEST MISTAKE
WASN'T LOSING,
IT WAS GETTING CAUGHT UP
IN ALL HER STUPID DRAMA.
WELL, THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
TIME TO SNAP OUT OF IT
AND FOCUS ON CREATING FLAVOR.
I'M GONNA OWN COOKING.
- HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
IT'S ONLY BEEN TWO MINUTES.
THANKFULLY, THE POVERTY GOD
ISN'T HERE TO LAUGH AT ME.
- YOUR HAND'S COVERED
IN BANDAGES, HOW STUPID!
- ALL RIGHT.
GUESS I GIVE UP.
- ( doorbell ringing )
- SAMURAI PIZZA CATS. GOT YOUR
PIZZA HERE. THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- NO, THANK YOU.
I'LL START COOKING
TOMORROW INSTEAD.
IN THE MEANTIME, IT'S
PIZZA-PIZZA TIME.
PIZZA.
( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- THIS IS SO YUMMY.
WHO EATS SOMEONE ELSE'S PIZZA
WITHOUT ASKING FIRST?
- HEY, IT WAS JUST ONE PIECE.
AND IT'S NOT LIKE YOU WERE
GONNA EAT THE WHOLE THING.
I HAVEN'T EATEN ANYTHING
SINCE YESTERDAY.
- BESIDES, I MEAN, AFTER
SUCH TERRIBLE TREATMENT...
- HUH?
- YOU BUTCHERED A KITCHEN,
BUT WON'T FEED ME.
- SHUT UP. LIKE YOU HAVE
ANY ROOM TO TALK, WHACK JOB.
NOW, LET GO
OF MY FREAKING PIZZA.
- OH NO! THERE'S FRESHLY-BAKED
GOOEY CHEESE
PLUS TOPPINGS ALL OVER MY FACE!
- OH, CRAP. HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( moaning )
- WELL, STILL VERY YUMMY.
- GET OUT OF MY HOUSE.
- ( sighs ) ALL I WANTED
WAS SOME OF SUWANO'S COOKING.
- HA, I'D ONLY HEARD
STORIES MYSELF.
- BUT YOU REALLY ARE LOCKED
IN A KNOCK-DOWN-DRAG-OUT,
AREN'T YOU?
LONG TIME, NO SEE, MOMIJI.
- WHAT THE... KUROYURI?
HI, I GUESS.
WHY ARE YOU IN THE HUMAN REALM?
- WHY, TO HELP YOU OUT WITH
YOUR SITUATION, OF COURSE.
- DO, HUH?
- YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL
FOR OUR FRIENDSHIP.
I RECOMMENDED MYSELF
TO YAMABUKI JUST FOR YOU, HONEY.
I SAID TO HER, I SAID,
"YAMABUKI, I CAN'T LEAVE
ONE OF MY VERY BEST FRIENDS
HANGING ON HER MISSION."
THEN I TOLD HER I WAS THE
ONLY ONE IN THE WORLD
WHO COULD RESCUE YOU RIGHT NOW.
LUCKILY, SHE DECIDED
IT WOULD BE BEST,
IF I GOT DOWN HERE IN A HURRY
SO WE COULD JOIN FORCES.
WITH THAT BEING SAID,
I SO LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING
WITH YOU, HONEY BUNNY.
HMM, ALTHOUGH, I DON'T
HAVE THE LEAST BIT OF INTEREST
IN HELPING YOU OUT.
AS SOON AS I CAN MANAGE,
I'M GOING TO STEAL THIS LITTLE
ICHIKO'S HAPPINESS ENERGY
AND GET MYSELF
ALL THE CREDIT FOR IT.
ONCE I DO, YAMABUKI IS MOST
CERTAINLY GOING TO SAY,
- THAT WAS FANTASTIC, KUROYURI.
- GIRL, YOU KNOW HOW I DO.
- BOOGER! YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A BOOGER WOMAN.
- ( laughing ) KUROYURI,
YOU'RE THE SAME AS EVER.
- ( panting )
- YOUR STRENGTH IS STARTING
TO DECLINE, ISN'T IT, HONEY?
- DON'T CALL ME "HONEY,"
I WILL KILL YOU.
DANG IT, SHE'S MAKING
A FOOL OUT OF ME.
HOW CAN SOMEBODY
THAT LAZY BE THAT CLEVER?
UGH, I CAN'T FOR THE
LIFE OF ME FIGURE OUT
WHY SHE'S ONE OF
YAMABUKI'S FAVORITES,
BUT I'M GONNA DRAG THIS GIRL
DOWN AND TAKE HER OUT.
- I SEE YOU'RE STILL
FOSTERING THAT RIVALRY
FOR NO REASON, AS USUAL.
WHAT A PAIN IN THE BUTT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, THOUGH?
IT'S KINDA FUNNY.
I HAD NO IDEA
YOU WERE SO TERRIBLY
CONCERNED ABOUT ME.
I'M THANKFUL FOR YOUR HELP.
- ( chuckles )
NO PROBLEM.
WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
- MISSION ACCOMPLISHED!
- I CAN DO ANYTHING
I SET MY MIND TO.
MAYBE SOMETHING LIKE NEVER
SEEING THE POVERTY GOD AGAIN.
- UH, OH, IT'S THE POVERTY GOD.
- JINX, YOU BETTER
GET OUT OF MY KITCHEN!
- I'M A GOD NOT A JINX.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
OH MY GOODNESS,
LOOKS LIKE ANOTHER
POVERTY GOD IS MAKING A VISIT.
- ( gasps )
- SO THIS IS ICHIKO SAKURA.
WELL, IF APPEARANCES
AREN'T DECEIVING,
SHE HASN'T HAD ANY
DIFFICULTY WITH YOU.
- AWESOME, WHO IS THIS JOKER?
WAIT, DON'T TELL ME
YOU HAVE FRIENDS.
- I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS YOU CAN CALL HER
A FRIEND IF YOU WANT TO.
- HOWEVER...
- THIS IS WHAT YOU WOULD
CALL AN ALLIANCE.
- Both: IT'S TIME TO SAY
YOUR PRAYERS.
- ( screams )
- ( screaming )
- THE HELL. YOU BROKE IT,
KUROYURI.
- ARGH! DAMN, MOMIJI.
- OOPSIE. I SORTA FORGOT THAT
THE TRIAL CAKE I WAS MAKING
WAS STILL IN THE OVEN.
- TO MAKE A CAKE EXPLODE,
YOU MUST BE INCREDIBLY TALENTED.
- AW, HELL, NO. GODA.
SO, THE TWO OF YOU ARE TRYING
TO MAKE A FOOL OUT OF ME,
IS THAT RIGHT?
IF THAT'S HOW YOU WANT IT, THEN
WHO CARES ABOUT ANYONE ELSE?
I'M TURNING YOU
TWISTED SISTERS TO ASH.
WOOT. INTRODUCING POVERTY GOD
ITEM, THE "LEMME GO, GRANDPA!"
ACTIVATED BY CALLING
HIM "POCHI,"
WHICH MAKES HIM MAD, CAUSING
HIM TO REDUCE EVERYTHING
IN THE AREA TO ASHES.
PEE-YEW, WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
- ARGH!
WAY TO GO. YOU DISTRACTED ME
AND MADE ME BURN THE STEW.
- THAT'S WAY
BEYOND BURNT, HONEY.
AND DON'T BE SO QUICK
TO THROW IT OUT,
IT MIGHT STILL BE SALVAGEABLE.
- DISAGREE.
- I THINK PEOPLE STARVING
IN HELL WOULD TURN THIS DOWN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN? IT'S NOT
LIKE YOU CAN COOK EITHER.
I MEAN, UNLESS YOU CAN.
- DEFENSIVE ABOUT COOKING, MUCH?
WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
WAIT, I KNOW. WHY DON'T
WE HAVE A COOK-OFF?
COME ON, IT'LL BE LIKE A REMATCH
FOR THAT UNFORTUNATE
TENNIS GAME.
YOUR HAPPINESS ENERGY WILL STILL
BE ON THE LINE, NATURALLY.
- YEAH, OKAY, FINE BY ME.
AND IF I WIN, YOU'LL HAVE
TO LEAVE THE HUMAN REALM
FOR REAL AND FOREVER
THIS TIME, NO CHEATING.
- ( laughs )
- HEY, YOU GUYS?
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I WAS HALF-JOKING BECAUSE
OF YOUR SKILL SET.
I'M JUST CONFUSED WHERE
ALL YOUR RANDOM CONFIDENCE
IS COMING FROM.
- I GOT WHAT IT TAKES
WHEN IT'S GAME TIME, TRICK!
- DON'T IGNORE ME.
- GAME TIME, HOW CUTE.
THAT ONLY WORKS WHEN YOU
KNOW HOW TO PLAY THE GAME,
AND YOU DON'T EVEN
KNOW HOW TO COOK!
- SHUT UP, SHUT UP. SHUT UP!
HEY YOU, GREEN DRESS!
- WHAT?
- YOU GET TO BE THE JUDGE.
- WHAT? WHY ME? WHAT?
- BUT FIRST, TELL US WHAT
TYPE OF FOOD IS YOUR FAVORITE.
THAT WAY WE CAN MAKE A DISH
TO SUIT WHAT YOU'D LIKE BEST.
SO WHAT DO YOU LIKE TO EAT?
- UM, LET ME THINK.
MEAT AND TATERS?
- UGH, WHY ME?
- YOUR HATRED OF LOSING
IS WORKING AGAINST YOU, ICHIKO!
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH
HAPPINESS ENERGY YOU HAVE,
IT'S NOT GONNA MAKE YOU
A SKILLED COOK OVERNIGHT.
BUT COOKING IS MY SPECIALTY!
THIS CONTEST IS MINE.
THERE, I'M ALL DONE! AND
LET THIS BE A LESSON TO YOU!
- SO, UH, WHAT WAS YOURS? STEW?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
- NO, I WOULD SAY NO.
- IT'S MEAT AND POTATO
STEW, HELLO.
- UM, I THINK YOU MEAN
BLACK CHARCOAL STEW, HELLO.
YOU KNOW, AT THE RIGHT ANGLE,
IT KINDA LOOKS LIKE A
SCREAMING FACE.
- QUIT YOUR YAPPING,
AND JUDGE IT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "JUDGE IT?"
IT'S NOT EVEN MEAT AND POTATOES!
I'M NOT ENTIRELY CONVINCED WHAT
I'M LOOKING AT IS EVEN FOOD.
- OH, COME ON. WHETHER
YOU'RE JUDGING FOOD OR PEOPLE,
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU SEE
THAT MATTERS, IT'S THE INSIDE.
- SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS,
YOU'RE BASICALLY A
FAILURE AS A HUMAN BEING?
- UGH, THIS IS GROSS.
WHAT CHOICE DO I HAVE?
I'LL JUDGE IT.
AND THEN I CAN
JUST SAY SHE'S LOST.
- ( screaming )
HELP ME.
( screaming )
- ( screaming )
- ( machine gun firing )
- ( screaming loudly )
- IT TASTED SO BAD
SHE WENT BACK TO HEAVEN.
- WELL, THAT WAS RUDE OF HER.
- HOW DO WE KNOW WHO WON THE
CONTEST NOW? WHAT DO WE DO?
- I THINK YOU SHOULD
FINISH IT OFF.
- NO THANKS.
I'M NOT READY TO DIE, YET.
- HMM. I TRIED.
- WELCOME BACK.
I'D LIKE TO GET THAT DETAILED
REPORT YOU PROMISED ME.
WHAT IS YOUR ANALYSIS
OF MOMIJI'S CURRENT SITUATION?
IS THE HUMAN REALM
TOO MUCH FOR HER?
- TAKING OUT ICHIKO SAKURA
IS WAY MORE THAN I CAN HANDLE.
I THINK MOMIJI IS DOING
AN INCREDIBLE JOB!
- HOW CAN ONE GIRL
CAUSE SO MUCH DRAMA?
- I'LL TRY COOKING
AGAIN TOMORROW.
- WHY? I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYTHING BETTER THAN PIZZA.
- OMG, I STILL HAVEN'T BEEN
ABLE TO STOP LAUGHING.
- ( laughs )