Narrator: FROM THE
BEGINNING OF TIME,
THIS WORLD HAS BEEN
CONSIDERED DIVINE.
FROM THE MOUNTAINS TO THE SEAS,
DOWN TO EACH SOLITARY TREE,
IT IS BELIEVED THERE
DWELLS A DEITY
WITHIN EACH AND EVERYTHING.
WHAT IS NOT KNOWN, HOWEVER, IS
THAT AMONG ALL OF THESE DEITIES,
THERE IS A POVERTY GOD REALM,
WHEREIN DWELLS THE
GODS OF DESTITUTION.
- UNFORTUNATELY, THE BALANCE OF
FORTUNE WITHIN THE HUMAN REALM
IS CURRENTLY ASKEW.
IT IS OUR ROLE, AS POVERTY GODS,
TO PRESERVE THAT
PRECIOUS EQUILIBRIUM.
MOMIJI, PLEASE GO TO THE HUMAN
REALM AND FIX THIS AT ONCE.
- ( groaning )
DO I HAVE TO?
SOUNDS LIKE A PAIN.
- SHE CAN NEVER JUST SAY YES.
WELL, THAT MAY BE THE CASE.
BUT, IT'S STILL YOUR
ASSIGNMENT TODAY.
- ( gasps )
RUDE.
WHY DOES THIS GIRL HAVE
WATERMELONS IN HER SWEATER?
I MEAN, THOSE CANNOT BE REAL.
THEY'RE RIDICULOUS. THEY'VE
GOTTA BE FAKE!
I HATE THIS GIRL
AND HER STUPID CHEST!
- OH, STOP BEING JEALOUS.
JUST SUCK IT UP, GET DOWN THERE,
AND TAKE CARE OF THE SOURCE OF
ALL THIS MIXED UP FORTUNE.
HER NAME IS ICHIKO SAKURA.
- FINE, I'LL GO. I GUESS
I DON'T HAVE MUCH OF A CHOICE.
- THANK YOU
FOR YOUR POSITIVE ATTITUDE.
- OH, YEAH.
HEY, WHILE I'M GONE,
TRY NOT TO FORGET TO RECORD
ONEGAI RANKING FOR ME, OKAY?
- QUIT PROCRASTINATING AND GO!
- HAVE A GOOD DAY, MISS ICHIKO.
- THANKS! WELL, I GUESS I'M OFF!
- All: HEY, ICHIKO!
GOOD MORNING!
- MORNING, BOYS.
- All: HAVE A GREAT DAY!
- Both: WE HAVE YOUR SLIPPERS
FOR YOU!
- YOUR BAG, MISS?
- THANK YOU.
- THAT'S CORRECT!
- ( all gasping )
- ( screaming )
- ( all exclaiming )
- ( laughing )
- Ichiko: SO TRUE.
- Akane: GOD, I CANNOT STAND
ICHIKO SAKURA.
- Ai: YOU MEAN TIT-CHIKO?
TALK ABOUT OVERBOARD, RIGHT?
IF SHE'S GONNA BE THAT STACKED
SHE SHOULD AT LEAST BE DUMB.
- SERIOUSLY, WHAT THE HELL?
I WISH SHE WOULD DO US A FAVOR
AND DIE ALREADY.
- Ai: GETTING POSSESSED
BY A DEMON WOULD BE FINE, TOO.
- ( girls laughing )
- ( laughing loudly )
COMMONERS PATHETICALLY
LOOKING UP FROM BELOW
WILL NEVER CEASE TO CRACK ME UP!
MY FAVORITE PART IS
THEY DON'T EVEN REALIZE
THEIR PETTY JEALOUSIES ONLY END
UP SERVING AS MY DRIVING FORCE!
I CAN'T BLAME THEM.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
I'M 16 YEARS OLD,
MY LIFE HAS NEVER BEEN ANYTHING
LESS THAN LUCKY!
I'M PRETTY, I DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT MONEY,
AND I'VE NEVER HAD TO WORK
FOR ANYTHING, LIKE, EVER!
EVERY LIGHT IN FRONT OF ME
IS GREEN!
EVERYTHING IN MY LIFE IS COMING
UP ROSES, AS THEY SAY!
NOBODY EVER SAID LIFE WAS
EXACTLY AN EQUAL PROPOSITION
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S MY FAULT
THEIR FORTUNE MAKES
THEM ORDINARY.
( gasping )
IT'S GONE!
WHAT THE... WHAT WAS THAT?
- FORTUNATE GIRLS WHO HAVE
SUCH LITTLE CONCERN FOR OTHERS,
NEED A LESSON IN MISFORTUNE.
I HAVE COME TO THIS REALM
TO FORCE YOU BACK
ONTO EQUAL FOOTING
WITH THE REST OF HUMANITY.
DOES THAT WORK FOR YOU?
- ( bell ringing )
- WHERE'D SHE GO?
- WHAT! WHAT! WHAT!
WHAT THE... WHAT WAS THAT?
- HEY, SLOW DOWN THERE!
NO RUNNING IN THE HALL!
- I'M SORRY. PLEASE,
YOU HAVE TO HELP ME, SIR.
THERE IS A MAJOR PERVERT
IN THE GIRLS' BATHROOM!
- All: WHAT!
( clamoring )
- GET BACK TO CLASS, NOW!
SEE, THERE'S NO PERVERT IN HERE.
OKAY, YOU GUYS,
GO BACK TO CLASS.
- Suwano: GOOD EVENING,
MISS ICHIKO.
THE BATH IS EXACTLY THE WAY
YOU LIKE IT.
- YEAH, COOL. THANKS, SUWANO.
( sighs )
I WONDER WHAT ON EARTH
THAT THING COULD'VE BEEN.
IT WASN'T MY IMAGINATION.
I'M NOT A CRAZY PERSON.
- ( water bubbling )
- ( chuckling )
IS THIS CLICHE OR WHAT?
- ( grunting )
- HUH?
- ( Ichiko screaming )
- DON'T WORRY, MISS ICHIKO!
I'M HERE FOR YOU!
- NO SICKOS IN MY BATHROOM!
AND STAY OUT!
- ALL RIGHT. I CAN PLAY.
- ( banging on door )
- Momiji: KNOCK KNOCK.
WHO'S THERE?
THE QUEEN OF
THE POVERTY GOD REALM, MOMIJI!
PLEASE, COME IN!
WHY, THANK YOU!
- ( making spooky sounds )
- ( gasping )
GET OUT OF HERE, JERK MONSTER!
- OH, NO, BUMMER!
YOU CAN'T TOUCH ME WHEN
I'M IN MY SPIRIT FORM!
( laughs )
BUT THEN AGAIN. I CAN'T REALLY
DO ANYTHING, EITHER.
- ( panting )
WHAT THE HELL?
OKAY, WHO EXACTLY ARE YOU?
- MY NAME'S MOMIJI,
AND I'M A POVERTY GOD.
I'M FROM THE LAND OF THE GODS.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, FROM ON HIGH.
- YOU'RE A GOD OF POVERTY?
- I AM.
- SO. WHAT DID YOU
COME TO MY HOUSE FOR?
- WELL. I'M HERE FOR YOU.
I'VE BEEN ORDERED TO TURN YOU
INTO A REGULAR PERSON.
- MORE LIKE HERE
TO MAKE ME LOOK STUPID.
- OH, YEAH, THAT LEVEL
IS OUT OF CONTROL.
WHAT'S WORSE IS YOU'RE
ABSORBING HAPPINESS ENERGY
FROM EVERYONE AROUND YOU.
- NOTHING YOU SAY MAKES SENSE!
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT
WITH THIS ANYWAY?
( gasps )
- ONLY HAPPINESS AND UNHAPPINESS
ENERGY LEVELS, DUH.
- GROSS, THIS THING IS FILTHY.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT,
NOW LISTEN TO ME CAREFULLY.
EVERY LIVING THING INHERENTLY
HAS A QUANTITY OF ENERGY
THAT BRINGS THEM GOOD FORTUNE,
WHICH WE CALL HAPPINESS ENERGY.
BY CONTRAST, ENERGY THAT BRINGS
ABOUT CALAMITY TO ONE'S SELF
IS UNHAPPINESS ENERGY.
CURRENTLY, THE BALANCE
OF THESE TWO ENERGIES
IN THIS PARTICULAR TOWN
IS RIDICULOUSLY OUT OF WHACK.
THE CAUSE OF THIS,
ICHIKO SAKURA, IS YOU.
- SORRY. BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN BY THAT.
- I'M NOT SURE HOW IT HAPPENED,
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST CALL IT
A DIVINE MISHAP?
BASICALLY, SOMEONE
SCREWED UP ALL OVER YOU
AND GAVE YOU TOO MUCH
HAPPINESS ENERGY.
WAY MORE THAN NORMAL,
AND, AS IF THAT WASN'T ENOUGH,
YOU'RE ABSORBING THE ENERGY
OF THOSE AROUND YOU,
( menacingly ) WHICH IS
CAUSING TROUBLE FOR EVERYONE.
- SO, AFTER MY HAPPINESS ENERGY
GOES DOWN TO NORMAL
AND THERE'S NO MORE
FORTUNE TROUBLE OR WHATEVER,
LIKE, WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO ME?
- LET ME SHOW YOU.
HELLO, THIS IS
YOUR NEWSCASTER, MOMIJI.
ICHIKO, WHO FAILS TO BE
ACCEPTED
INTO ANY OF THE COLLEGES
TO WHICH SHE'S APPLIED
WILL, IN THE NEAR FUTURE,
LOSE HER HOME,
FINDING HERSELF
OUT ON THE STREETS.
LUCKILY, SHE WILL BE TAKEN
IN BY A KIND MAN,
PARENTHETICAL SNICKER,
WHOM SHE WILL LATER MARRY.
TOGETHER, THEY WILL HAVE
FIVE CHILDREN
AND BUILD A WARM FAMILY,
PARENTHETICAL GUFFAW!
- Ichiko: I LOOK
LIKE A DISASTER!
- OH, YEAH, YOU DO. THOSE KIDS
ARE GONNA TAKE THEIR TOLL.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M HOPING FOR.
- WHY DO YOU WANT THAT FOR ME?
- MAYBE NOT EXACTLY.
BUT SOMETHING CLOSE.
WE HAVE A DIFFERENT ISSUE
AT HAND, THOUGH.
IT MAY NOT BE ON PURPOSE,
BUT YOU NEED TO KNOW
IF YOU KEEP ABSORBING HAPPINESS
ENERGY FROM OTHERS,
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE
PEOPLE AROUND YOU MISERABLE.
- ESPECIALLY THE ONES
YOU CARE ABOUT.
- ( gasps )
- MY OBJECTIVE WITH YOU
IS TWO-FOLD.
ONE, TAKE AWAY
THAT NASTY HABIT YOU HAVE
OF CONSUMING EVERYONE ELSE'S
HAPPINESS ENERGY.
AND TWO, REMOVE YOUR
RIDICULOUS AMOUNT OF FORTUNE.
THEN, EVERYTHING WILL RETURN
TO THE WAY IT SHOULD BE.
- OKAY, I THINK I'VE HEARD
ABOUT ENOUGH OF THIS!
YOU THINK I WANT MY LIFE TO SUCK
SO EVERYONE ELSE CAN
BE HAPPY INSTEAD?
HOW DOES THAT MAKE SENSE,
POVERTY GOD?
( chuckling )
YOU MAY BE A GODDESS
OR WHATEVER.
BUT ARE YOU SURE YOU
HAVEN'T CONFUSED
BEING A GOD OF FLAT-BROKENESS
WITH FLAT-CHESTEDNESS?
- ( laughing maniacally )
I CAN SUCK ALL THAT FAT OUT
OF YOUR CHEST, IF YOU WANT.
- OOH, SENSITIVE!
- YOUR CONSENT IS NOT A FACTOR.
I WILL EXECUTE MY DUTY
BY FORCE IF I HAVE TO.
- EW. DON'T POINT
YOUR CREEPY PLUSHY AT ME.
- THIS IS AN OFFICIAL
POVERTY GOD ITEM.
- UM, HELLO! MISS SAKURA?
IT'S ABOUT TIME
FOR YOUR DEATH INJECTION!
- YOU JUST MADE THAT UP,
DIDN'T YOU?
- SO I'M GONNA USE THIS TO
SUCK OUT YOUR HAPPINESS ENERGY.
- YOU WHAT?
HOLD ON, YOU CAN'T SERIOUSLY BE
PLANNING TO STICK ME WITH THAT!
- OH, NOW, CALM DOWN, MY DEAR.
THIS THING IS DESIGNED
TO GUARANTEE
THAT YOU FEEL THE PAIN!
TAKE IT!
- WHAT ARE YOU, CRAZY?
IT'S ALIVE!
- NICELY DONE, KUMAGAI!
HOLD HER DOWN!
- LET GO. NO!
- OOPS.
KUMAGAI, MOVE AWAY
FROM THE LIGHT!
YOU STILL AREN'T GIVING ME
ENOUGH CREDIT, ICHIKO.
YOUR WOOD CAN'T STOP ME!
- WILL YOU GET OUT
OF MY HOUSE ALREADY?
- SAY, "AH."
- ( panting )
TAKE THAT.
STUPID POVERTY GOD.
SUWANO?
- HMM?
- SUWANO, WAKE UP.
- WHAT AM I DOING OUT HERE?
- I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR QUESTIONS.
JUST HURRY UP
AND GET RID OF THESE.
- GET RID OF THEM?
I HAVE TO SAY, I'M A FAN OF YOUR
FRIEND'S CUTE LITTLE COSTUME.
- WILL YOU QUIT BEING
A DIRTY OLD MAN AND FOCUS?
- ( Momiji sighing )
CLEVER GIRL.
DON'T GO GETTING IT IN YOUR HEAD
THAT I'M JUST GONNA GIVE UP
ON YOU, THOUGH.
YEAH, I KNOW. THANKS.
MAYBE THIS CHICK'S
A REINCARNATION
OF A GOD OF FORTUNE.
HEY, BUDDY, HOW
ABOUT INSTEAD OF SMILING,
YOU CONCENTRATE ON DRIVING
AND MINDING YOUR OWN BUSINESS?
- I'M SORRY
IF I SEEM DISTRACTED.
IT'S JUST THAT THIS IS
THE FIRST TIME
MISS ICHIKO HAS BROUGHT HOME
A FRIEND TO PLAY WITH.
- I'M NOT HER FRIEND.
SO, I GUESS YOU MUST BE
HER BUTLER THEN?
MUST SUCK TO BE YOU.
CAN'T BE EASY TAKING CARE
OF THAT BRAT. YOU'RE A SAINT.
- NO, NO, QUITE THE OPPOSITE,
IN FACT.
I WAS ACTUALLY THERE
THE DAY MISS ICHIKO WAS BORN,
AND I CONSIDER MYSELF
RATHER LUCKY TO HAVE SERVED HER.
THROUGH 16 YEARS OF BOTH
THE GOOD TIMES AND THE BAD.
SHE'S GIVEN ME PRECIOUS MEMORY
AFTER PRECIOUS MEMORY.
I'M VERY GRATEFUL TO HER.
I MUST ASK YOU TO PLEASE
CONTINUE BEING HER FRIEND.
I'M NOT HER FRIEND, YO!
- LET ME TELL YOU
A LITTLE SECRET.
THAT GIRL
IS A VERY LONELY PERSON.
- ( yawning )
WELL, THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
- BY THE WAY...
WHERE IS IT
THAT I'M TAKING YOU, EXACTLY?
- YOU'RE ASKING ME NOW?
- ( door opening )
- Suwano: I'M BACK, MISS ICHIKO.
- UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES IS THAT
GIRL ALLOWED TO COME BACK HERE.
- OH, THERE YOU GO AGAIN, MISS.
SHE SEEMS LIKE SHE IS
A VERY GOOD FRIEND TO YOU.
- SHE'S NOT MY FRIEND, OKAY?
- ( sighing )
( groaning )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- NOTHING, I'M FINE.
NOW, TOMORROW IS YOUR BIRTHDAY,
IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY?
- OH, YEAH, I GUESS IT IS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE WHAT YOU
MAKE. I'M SURE IT'LL BE TASTY.
- I'LL DO MY BEST. THIS YEAR,
I THINK I'LL MAKE SOMETHING AS
SWEET AS YOU ARE.
- Ishida: MISS SAKURA!
- All: WE ALL WANT TO WISH YOU
A HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MISS ICHIKO!
- Suzuki: WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU GUYS THINK YOU'RE DOING?
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO PERFORM...
- SHUT UP!
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE OF CLASS!
- ( sighs )
THAT POVERTY GOD IS THE WORST.
NOW I'M BUMMED ON MY BIRTHDAY.
- ( laughing )
SETUP COMPLETE.
THIS SHOULD SHRED THAT SMUGNESS
RIGHT OFF HER LUCKY FACE.
THE POVERTY GOD ITEM,
GABRIEL TWO THOUSAND ELEVEN,
A NIFTY DEVICE WHICH ABSORBS
HAPPINESS ENERGY,
WHILE ALSO INFLICTING
HORRIFYING PAIN!
- ( door opens )
- PLEASE EX-SQUEEZE
MY CRUDE INTRUSION.
( gasps )
- ( breathing faintly )
- THAT'S NOT GOOD.
- ( glass shattering )
- ( all gasping )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- WOAH!
- WHAT? WAIT. KUMAGAI, RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT COULD HAVE HAPPENED?
DID THE POVERTY GOD HURT HIM?
PLEASE, PLEASE LET HIM BE OKAY!
- ( sighing )
I WISH, I WISH
I'D KILLED THAT LITTLE...
NO, MOMIJI. KEEP IT PG.
- Ichiko:
ACUTE CARDIAC INFARCTION?
- Male doctor: YES.
WE HAVE TO OPERATE IMMEDIATELY.
- HOWEVER, YOU SHOULD
PREPARE YOURSELF FOR THE WORST.
DOES HE HAVE ANY FAMILY?
- NO, HE DOESN'T.
HIS WIFE PASSED AWAY
FOUR YEARS AGO,
SO IT'S JUST BEEN THE TWO
OF US SINCE THEN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, SUWANO?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
LYING IN THAT BED?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE AT HOME,
WITH ME.
( gasps )
EW, TOO SWEET.
HOW MUCH SUGAR DID THAT MAN
PUT IN HERE ANYWAY?
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
IT'S WAY TOO BIG.
I'LL HAVE TO HAVE A TALK
WITH HIM WHEN HE COMES HOME.
IF HE COMES HOME.
HE HAS TO.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
Young Ichiko:
I HATE MOMMY AND DADDY!
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY!
THIS HAPPENED LAST YEAR,
AND IT HAPPENED
THE YEAR BEFORE THAT, TOO!
IT'S LIKE THEY DON'T EVEN CARE
ABOUT ME.
YOU WON'T EVER LEAVE ME,
WILL YOU, SUWANO?
- OF COURSE I WON'T.
NO MATTER WHAT, I WILL ALWAYS BE
RIGHT BY YOUR SIDE, MISS ICHIKO.
- NO.
( sobbing )
SUWANO, PLEASE DON'T DIE ON ME.
PLEASE, YOU JUST CAN'T DIE.
- ( pop )
- ( gasps )
- TOO SWEET. THIS MUST BE
WHAT DIABETES TASTES LIKE!
- GREAT, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- EATING CAKE, OBVIOUSLY.
- YOU HURT SUWANO, DIDN'T YOU?
- I DIDN'T.
- I KNOW YOU DID! YOU HAD
TO, THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT!
- NO, IT'S NOT.
BUT IT IS YOURS.
I TRIED TO WARN YOU,
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
YOU'VE BEEN SLOWLY ABSORBING
HIS HAPPINESS ENERGY
THE WHOLE TIME
YOU'VE LIVED TOGETHER,
IT'S COMPLETELY GONE NOW.
HE ONLY HAS UNHAPPINESS
ENERGY LEFT.
- YOU THINK I WANT
MY LIFE TO SUCK
SO EVERYONE ELSE CAN
BE HAPPY INSTEAD?
HOW DOES THAT MAKE SENSE?
- IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
HAPPINESS IS SOMETHING THAT
SHOULD BE SHARED.
I MEAN, DOES IT REALLY MATTER
HOW BIG AND WONDERFUL
THIS BIRTHDAY CAKE IS
IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANYONE ELSE
TO EAT IT WITH?
- NO. JUST STOP IT.
I DON'T NEED TO HEAR
ABOUT BEING UNHAPPY.
LEAST OF ALL FROM YOU!
( gasps )
- IF YOU ASK ME,
YOU'RE NOT UNHAPPY ENOUGH YET.
BUT, IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU CAN MAKE SURE
NO ONE ELSE AROUND YOU
SUFFERS THE WAY YOUR
BUTLER HAS, RIGHT?
- YEAH, OKAY, I GET IT.
GO AHEAD,
DO WHAT YOU CAME HERE TO DO.
- YOU HAVE
CHOSEN WISELY, ICHIKO.
THAT'S AN AMAZING AMOUNT.
NICELY DONE.
THE UNHAPPINESS ENERGY
YOU'VE BEEN SUPPRESSING
IS GOING TO BRING SOME
MISFORTUNE FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
BUT, OVER TIME,
AS YOU ACQUIRE MORE VIRTUE,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO HAVE THE SAME
LIFE AS OTHER NORMAL PEOPLE.
- GREAT, SOUNDS GREAT.
I WAS ACTUALLY
GETTING KINDA TIRED
OF ALL THE SPECIAL TREATMENT,
SO HOORAY FOR ME.
WHAT A GREAT LESSON.
- HUH?
- THAT WAS A LIE, BONEHEAD!
YOU'RE SUCH AN IDIOT!
WHY SHOULD I GIVE UP
MY HAPPINESS TO YOU
WHEN I CAN GIVE IT
TO WHOEVER I WANT. HA! BYE!
- ( door closing )
- ( bell ringing )
- ( embarrassed chuckle )
IS WHAT JUST HAPPENED
WHAT I THINK JUST HAPPENED?
GIRL, YOU HAVE DRIVEN ME
TO THE EDGE.
YOU'VE ONLY YOURSELF TO BLAME.
NOW I'M PISSED!
( yelling )
- ( explosion )
- ( gasps )
- ( yelling )
- ( cats screeching )
- ( screaming )
POVERTY GOD HAS LOST IT!
- I'M DONE TRYING TO TAKE AWAY
YOUR HAPPINESS.
INSTEAD, I'LL KILL YOU!
- ( bell ringing )
- THAT'S THE JOB OF A GRIM
REAPER, NOT A POVERTY GOD.
- I DON'T CARE!
IF I DON'T TAKE HER OUT,
MY SOUL IS GONNA SNAP!
CHARGE!
- ( screaming )
- ( meowing )
- ( panting )
ALMOST TO THE OPERATING ROOM!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
I SUPPOSE YOUR PLAN
IS TO SAVE MR. SUWANO WITH THAT.
- ( chuckles )
SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS
I CAN USE THIS TO SAVE HIM.
I ACTUALLY WASN'T EVEN SURE
WHETHER THAT WAS POSSIBLE.
- WHOOPSIE.
- EITHER WAY,
YOU'RE TOO LATE TO STOP ME NOW!
( yelling )
- ( glass shattering )
- MUST BE THURSDAY. I NEVER
COULD GET THE HANG OF THURSDAYS.
- Man: WHAT THE...
- THEY'RE FOUR-LEAF CLOVERS,
YAY!
- ( gasping )
- Female nurse:
DOCTOR, WE'RE LOSING HIM!
- Doctor: THIS MIGHT BE IT.
- ( phone ringing )
- Ichiko: SUWANO.
SUWANO.
- Both: PLEASE, SUWANO.
HANG IN THERE!
- AH, LOVELY.
A PAIR OF MISS ICHIKOS ARE HERE.
- Ichiko and young Ichiko:
YOU HAVE TO COME BACK TO US.
IF YOU DON'T. THERE'S GOING TO
BE SOME SERIOUS HELL TO PAY.
- ( machine beeping )
- ( gasping )
- I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE,
MISS ICHIKO.
I'VE GONE AND RUINED
YOUR BIRTHDAY
INSTEAD OF MAKING IT SPECIAL.
- WHAT WAS I SO WORRIED ABOUT?
YOU SEEM PERFECTLY
HEALTHY TO ME.
- I WILL ACCEPT ANY PUNISHMENT
YOU FEEL APPROPRIATE.
- OKAY.
I THINK I'VE GOT SOMETHING.
- YES?
AS OF TODAY, YOU'RE FIRED.
- FINE.
WHAT?
- THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU BARGE IN ON ME
WHILE I'M BATHING,
YOU HAVE A HEART ATTACK
AND ALMOST DIE ON MY BIRTHDAY,
AND YOUR CAKE IS TOO SWEET.
AND IF YOU TRY HARD...
( emotionally ) AND IF YOU TRY
REALLY HARD,
YOU COULD PROBABLY LIVE, LIKE,
ANOTHER 30 YEARS, YOU KNOW?
SO MOVE. THERE'S BETTER AIR
OUT IN THE COUNTRY.
YOU CAN FIND SOMEONE NEW
AND MARRY HER, OKAY?
- MISS ICHIKO.
I CAN'T EXPRESS MY GRATITUDE.
- I JUST FIRED YOU, FOR GOODNESS
SAKE! YOU SHOULD BE MAD AT ME!
- I SHOULD?
- YES!
- OF COURSE, I AM, BUT...
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS,
I JUST WANTED TO SAY THANK YOU.
FOR ALWAYS TAKING CARE OF ME.
- THAT GOES DOUBLE FOR ME.
THIS IS FOR THE BEST, RIGHT?
IF HE STAYS WITH ME FOR TOO
LONG, IT COULD HAPPEN AGAIN.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I MEAN, I'VE KINDA BEEN
ON MY OWN ANYWAY.
I'LL BE FINE.
YEAH, NO BIG DEAL.
THAT POVERTY GOD
HASN'T SHOWN UP AGAIN.
I WONDER IF SHE WENT HOME.
ONE WEEK DOWN.
BEING ALONE ISN'T SO BAD
ONCE YOU'RE USED TO IT.
MAN, IT'S GOOD TO BE HOME!
- WELCOME BACK, SWEETIE!
ARE YOU HUNGRY? OR WOULD
YOU RATHER TAKE A BATH?
OH, I KNOW WHAT YOU REALLY,
REALLY WANT.
READY TO BE UNHAPPY?
- ( both laughing )
- REALLY? I WANT ( angrily )
TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING HERE!
- ( sighs )
THAT HAPPINESS ENERGY IS BACK
UP TO WHERE IT WAS BEFORE.
- HUH?
- AS YOU CAN SEE ON
THIS HIGH TECH DIAGRAM,
MOST OF THE ENERGY YOU RELEASED
WOUND UP COMING
RIGHT BACK TO YOU.
- OH, WOW. LET ME GUESS
WHAT THAT MEANS.
- ONE MORE TIME.
YOU DON'T MIND?
- NO, THANKS!
- DON'T YOU '"NO, THANKS" ME!
- YOU WANT SOME OF THIS, GOD?
- SHUT UP! DON'T ASK FOR
SOMETHING YOU CAN'T HANDLE!
- GO AHEAD AND TAKE YOUR BEST
SHOT! I GOT NOTHING TO LOSE!
- STUPID POVERTY GOD!
- GIMME SOME OF THOSE BOOBS!
- Man: EXCUSE ME.
- LIKE YOU'D KNOW WHAT TO DO!
- EXCUSE ME.
- Both: WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S A SPECIAL DELIVERY.
- OH! IT'S FROM SUWANO!
- Suwano: WE'RE
GETTING MARRIED!
- ( church bell ringing )
- Ichiko and Momiji:
THAT WAS FAST!
- Students: THIS WEEK'S...
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO!
- SORRY TO KEEP
YOU WAITING, EVERYBODY!
DID YOU SEE MY CHARMING EXPLOITS
IN THIS EPISODE?
I'M SURE YOU DID, BUT JUST IN
CASE, HERE'S ANOTHER LOOK!
DID YOU SEE ME STANDING OVER
THERE? I'M SO CUTE, LIKE, RIGHT?
( laughing )