THE TOWN OF BUTSUMETSU.
OH, THIS IS IT.
I CAN FEEL IT IN MY BONES.
YOU'RE HERE SOMEWHERE.
AND I WILL FIND YOU, ONE
WAY OR ANOTHER.
- HEY, GOOD MORNING!
HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
- OH, I'M FINE, THANKS.
- YOU LOOK PRETTY, ICHIKO.
- YEAH. I KNOW.
- WHY, GOOD MORNING,
MISS SAKURA!
( giggles )
- ( gasps )
( screaming )
- Momiji: FOR THE LAST TIME.
I'VE GOT A LOT OF IRONS
IN THE FIRE WITH HER,
I JUST NEED SOME TIME
TO GET IT DONE.
BUT IF YOU DON'T STOP CONSTANTLY
PRESSURING ME,
I'M PROBABLY GONNA
GIVE UP ON THE WHOLE SHEBANG.
- YOU ARE A GOD. AND AS SUCH,
YOU KNOW YOU SHOULDN'T STAY DOWN
THERE IN THE HUMAN REALM
FOR TOO LONG.
YOU COULD CHANGE THE ENERGY
BALANCE, AND THAT'S A NO NO.
- THEN YOU SHOULD ALLOW ME
TO TAKE MORE ACTIVE MEASURES
SO I CAN GET OUT OF HERE!
SNEAKING AROUND ISN'T MY STYLE,
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING HIDING
FROM MY OWN SHADOW!
- THAT LITTLE...
( sighs )
LISTEN CAREFULLY. IF YOU CAN
MANAGE TO KEEP FROM REVEALING
THAT YOU'RE A POVERTY GOD OR
WHAT YOU'RE REALLY THERE TO DO,
I'LL GO AHEAD AND GIVE
YOU A BREAK THIS TIME.
- DOES THAT MEAN I CAN KILL HER?
- WHAT? NO! WHAT?
YOUR OBJECTIVE IS TO SEIZE
ICHIKO SAKURA'S HAPPINESS ENERGY
AND KEEP IT UNDER CONTROL...
- SORRY, LOSING YOU.
UNDER A BRIDGE.
OKAY. LET'S GO.
- AND NOW, OUR TRANSFER STUDENT
WILL INTRODUCE HERSELF.
- Momiji: THIS IS A PAIN.
- NO, IT'S NOT.
- HELLO, EVERYONE,
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS MOMIJI HINKONGAWA.
OKAY, LET'S SEE...
HOBBIES, I LIKE TO COSPLAY,
AND MY FAVORITE WORD IS FETTERS
BECAUSE, LIKE MY HUMILITY,
IT IS AWESOME.
I LIKE BOYS THAT
ARE INTO GIRLS LIKE ME,
CUZ I DON'T WANNA, LIKE,
CHANGE OR ANYTHING.
I GUESS I'M COMPATIBLE
WITH PUSHOVERS.
- I THOUGHT SHE WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE A GOD!
WHAT IS SHE DOING
IN A FREAKING HIGH SCHOOL?
- MY PERIODS ARE PRETTY LIGHT,
AND I LIKE THAT A LOT.
MY FAVORITE SEXUAL POSITION
IS THE FRUIT LOOP.
- OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOUR LAST NAME ON THE
BOARD SAYS BINBODA.
- EH, WHO CARES?
WHAT'S IN A NAME, RIGHT?
- WELL, MISS BINBODA,
YOU SIT NEXT TO MISS SAKURA.
- HEY, GOOD MORNING.
PLEASURE TO MEET YOU!
- OH, NO, LET ME ASSURE YOU,
THE PLEASURE IS ALL MINE.
BY THE WAY, THAT WASHBOARD CHEST
OF YOURS IS PRACTICALLY CONCAVE.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
RECONSTRUCTIVE
SURGERY TO FIX IT?
- ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY THAT
MY BOOBIES ARE DEFORMED?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE YOUR
OWN GIANT DISFIGUREMENT
YOU SHOULD FOCUS ON. UNLESS
YOU WANNA GO INTO PORN.
MM-HMM.
- Homeroom teacher: HOLD UP.
WHERE ARE YOU TWO GOING?
- SO NOW, THE POVERTY GOD REJECT
HAS INFILTRATED MY SCHOOL.
YOU'RE GONNA TRY TO TAKE
MY HAPPINESS ENERGY
IF YOU GET THE
CHANCE. TRY AGAIN.
BECAUSE WHATEVER
YOU'VE GOT PLANNED
WON'T BE AS EASY AS YOU THINK.
- I HATE GYM. I WILL
NEVER NOT HATE GYM.
- FOR REAL, LIKE,
WHAT'S THE POINT?
- Ichiko: WHAT IS SHE UP TO?
- READY TO GO WHEN YOU ARE!
LET'S PLAY!
- Ichiko: NO ONE HERE HAS A
PROBLEM WITH WHAT SHE'S WEARING?
- Nakamura: HEY, MAI!
YOU CAN'T HOLD BACK ON HER JUST
BECAUSE SHE'S NEW, OKAY?
- I'M ALL OVER IT.
- Momiji: DIE!
- ( gasps )
( screams )
- OH! I'M SO SORRY!
- Ai: MISA! ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- Akane: WE'RE OKAY.
THANK GOD
THE BALL ONLY HIT YOU!
- Ai: DON'T WORRY ABOUT US, JUST
TRY TO BREATHE THROUGH THE PAIN!
- SHE IS SUCH A JERK!
- Science teacher: YOU
THERE! YOUNG MAN!
DON'T HORSE AROUND WHEN
THE BURNERS ARE LIT!
THERE ARE RULES FOR A REASON!
- UH?
( screaming )
- All: HUH?
- WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
ARE YOU OKAY?
- OH. NOTHING. THE FLAME JUST
BURNT MY NOTEBOOK A LITTLE.
- AW.
- THIS REEKS OF POVERTY GOD.
LIKE I'M GONNA FALL FOR THAT.
IT'S THE OLDEST TRICK
IN THE BOOK.
- OH, NO. SOME CARELESS
PERSON
ACCIDENTALLY ALMOST
MESSED YOU UP.
- ARE YOU TRYING TO KILL ME?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT? ME DEAD?
- Homeroom teacher: AND WITH
THAT, THE ENTRY IS REGISTERED...
- Ichiko: GET IT TOGETHER,
ICHIKO.
IF YOU LET POVERTY GOD ON
WHEELS TRIP YOU UP,
YOU'LL BE PLAYING RIGHT INTO HER
WEIRD LITTLE WRAPPED UP HAND.
- Homeroom teacher: ...BECAUSE
YOU'VE BEEN TAKING NOTES,
PAYING ATTENTION,
AND MUST CLEARLY...
- Ichiko: I CAN'T LOOK
AT IT. I WON'T LOOK AT IT.
I REFUSE TO LOOK AT IT!
OH, CRAP, I'M GONNA LOOK AT IT.
( screams )
YOU'RE A PEST, YOU KNOW THAT?
SOMEONE NEEDS TO
EXTERMINATE YOU!
- Miura: WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH ICHIKO?
- Hasegawa: SHE LOOKS
A LITTLE STRESSED OUT TODAY.
- DOESN'T SHE LIKE
THE NEW GIRL?
LOOKS LIKE SWEET TITS
AIN'T SO SWEET NO MO'.
- Ichiko: I'M EXHAUSTED.
I'VE LOST ALL OF MY
KEEP-IT-TOGETHER WILL POWER.
I HATE THAT POVERTY GOD!
SHE'S WALKING ALL OVER ME AND
RUINING EVERYTHING!
THE WHOLE CLASS IS
WONDERING WHAT'S UP
AND GOSSIPING ABOUT ME!
I'VE WORKED SO HARD TO GET
WHERE I AM IN THAT SCHOOL, TOO!
SHE'S MAKING MY WHOLE LIFE
A DISASTER!
I HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO GET RID OF HER
BEFORE SHE DRIVES ME INSANE.
( gasps )
- ( groaning )
THIS IS MUCH BAD. VERY BAD FOR
PRETTY GIRL. I AM MUCH HUNGRY.
I CANNOT TAKE ANOTHER STEP,
PLEASE. HELP.
- WHAT? WAIT, WHO ARE YOU?
- A FRIEND. OH,
BEAUTIFUL YOUNG LADY,
MEETING HERE MUST BE FATED
ENCOUNTER, YES.
- REALLY? 'CAUSE FATE
DOESN'T USUALLY GRAB MY LEG.
- PLEASE, I AM TRAVELING MONK.
I AM MUCH OBLIGED IF YOU COULD
FIND IT IN HEART CHEST
TO GIVE TO ME DINNER, BATH,
PLACE TO SLEEP,
RESTROOM, AND TOOTHBRUSH
TONIGHT, PLEASE, OH, PLEASE?
- YOU SURE DO ASK A LOT!
- I CAN'T HELP BUT TO TELL
TO YOU HOW AMAZING YOUR SKIN IS!
- PERVERTED MONK!
COME ON. I'M WAY OVER THIS DAY.
I MEAN, REALLY. NOTHING'S GONE
RIGHT SINCE THE PG SHOWED UP.
HEY, WHY IS MY ROOM A DISASTER?
ALL OF THESE WERE IN THE CLOSET
WHEN I LEFT.
- Momiji: UGH. QUIT BEING SUCH
A BABY. JUST DEAL WITH IT.
- CRAP. DON'T TELL ME...
- HOME IS WHERE YOU HANG YOUR
HAT, RIGHT? BEFORE LONG,
YOU'LL BE USED TO
HOW CRAMPED THIS IS.
- WELCOME HOME, NOBITA!
- DON'T TELL ME YOU THINK YOU'RE
A ROBOT CAT FROM THE FUTURE NOW!
- AH.
- EH.
- A POVERTY GOD ITEM! IT'S THE
TIMESPACE EXPANSION DEVICE.
THE FAMOUS LUCKY
MALLET CARPENTER.
- IT'S MY IMAGINATION.
NOTHING'S THERE.
- PORT SIDE. THE BARRAGE
IS WEAK AT BEST!
1501. 15...
OH, MY GOD!
YOU ALMOST SAW MY BOOBIES!
- I DON'T LIKE THIS.
- YOU KNOW WHAT,
YOU COULD AT LEAST KNOCK
BEFORE YOU OPEN THE DOOR.
NOW, TRY AGAIN!
- ( laughing maniacally )
WHAT AM I LAUGHING ABOUT?
I'M TOTALLY LOSING IT!
KEEP YOUR COOL,
STAY FOCUSED.
YOU CAN HANDLE THIS.
- Man: OH, MOMMA! OH...
- HUH?
- THERE'S NO QUESTION.
THAT'S THE SAME SMELL AS MOMMA.
OH, YEAH, IT'S SO GOOD! OHHH.
- KEEP YOUR COOL.
KEEP YOUR COOL. KEEP... HIYAH!
IT'S ONE THING AFTER ANOTHER!
WHAT'S NEXT?
I GET IT NOW! YOU'RE ONE OF
THE POVERTY GOD'S MINIONS!
- LOOK, JUST CALM DOWN
AND LISTEN TO ME, PLEASE!
JUDGING BY WHAT I
WITNESSED TODAY,
YOU'RE BEING HAUNTED
BY SOMETHING INHUMAN!
IF YOU STOP KILLING
ME FOR A SEC,
I CAN BE USEFUL, HELP YOU
GET RID OF IT,
I SWEAR!
SO YOUR NAME IS ICHIKO SAKURA.
A FINE NAME, INDEED.
MY NAME IS BOBBY, AND I'M ON
A PILGRIMAGE TO RID THE WORLD
OF ANY EVIL SPIRITS I FIND
THROUGHOUT MY JOURNEY.
- HOW MUCH IS HE GONNA EAT?
- I CAME TO THIS CITY BECAUSE
THERE WAS A FOUL PRESENCE
EMANATING FROM IT.
NOW WHEN I MET YOU THIS EVENING,
I COULD SEE THE PRESENCE HAD
ENCOMPASSED YOU.
IT CAUGHT MY ATTENTION, WHICH IS
WHY I FOLLOWED YOU HOME.
- HEY, WHY ARE YOU SPEAKING
NORMALLY NOW?
- OH! MY MAMA ALWAYS TOLD ME IF
I'M EVER IN TROUBLE JUST TO ACT
LIKE I COULD BARELY
SPEAK THE LANGUAGE,
AND SOMEONE WOULD BE MORE
LIKELY TO HELP!
- BRING YOUR MAMA HERE,
I CAN SET HER STRAIGHT!
THE POVERTY GOD ISN'T
AN EVIL SPIRIT. SHE'S A DEITY.
YOU'VE MIXED UP RELIGIONS.
- NOT TO WORRY, SUGAR.
SHINTO BUDDHISM SYNCRETISM.
THE GOD AMATERASU
BECAME VAIROCANA.
ALSO, THE GREAT HACHIMAN BECAME
TATHAGATA, BECAUSE IN JAPAN,
DEITIES AND BUDDHAS HAVE BOTH
BEEN CONSIDERED ONE AND THE SAME
EVER SINCE ANCIENT HISTORY.
WE ARE NOW IN WHAT IS KNOWN
AS THE LAND OF THE GODS,
AND HERE THERE IS NO SUCH THING
AS A WALL BETWEEN RELIGIONS.
- MEANING?
- MEANING THIS,
THAT YOU MAY BE BETTER SUITED TO
DRIVE THIS PARTICULAR BEING AWAY
THAN I AM, GIRL.
- COULD YOU EXPLAIN THAT MORE?
- AS I SAID BEFORE,
I CAME TO THIS CITY IN
SEARCH OF AN EVIL PRESENCE
I COULD SENSE DWELLING
WITHIN IT.
I'VE NOW LEARNED THAT PRESENCE
IS A FLAT-CHESTED GIRL
WITH HAIR DOWN IN HER EYES
FOR SOME REASON
THAT YOU CALL THE POVERTY GOD.
- I'LL KILL HIM!
- HOWEVER,
IT IS ALSO CERTAIN THERE IS A
SIMILAR ENERGY TO HERS,
ALBEIT NOT AS NEGATIVE,
COMING FROM YOU.
- WHAT? DON'T TELL ME YOU CAN
SEE MY HAPPINESS ENERGY, TOO!
- MY SPIRITUAL AWARENESS
IS EXTREMELY HIGH!
WELL, IT'S NOT CRYSTAL CLEAR,
BUT I CAN STILL VAGUELY
MAKE OUT SOMETHING
COVERING YOU,
SOMEWHERE AROUND... TITTY.
( chuckles )
I'M JOKING! IT WAS A JOKE, COME
ON! IT WAS AN ACCIDENT, I SWEAR!
MY HAND HAS A MIND OF
ITS OWN, BABY DOLL.
CONSIDER YOURSELF LUCKY
I STOPPED IT FROM GOING
WHERE IT WANTED TO!
LOOK, JUST DON'T BE SO
MAD AT ME, PRETTY PLEASE?
CAN'T WE HUG IT OUT?
- THE PROBLEM IS I AM
SO MAD AT YOU,
YOU PERVERTED, DEGENERATE MONK!
TWISTED JERK. IS
THERE ANYTHING YOU CAN DO
BESIDES GROPE TEENAGE GIRLS?
- NOT AS WELL, BUT...
THERE'S THIS.
- HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
- A MYSTICAL ITEM I MADE
TO VANQUISH EVIL SPIRITS.
THE SOMIN SHORAI!
SOMIN SHORAI IS
THE NAME OF A DEITY
THAT GRANTED DIVINE PROTECTION.
SPECIFICALLY TO WARD OFF
PLAGUE AND CALAMITY
FROM THE GOD, SUSANOWO.
SINCE YOU CLEARLY HAVE
MORE SPIRIT POWER THAN ME,
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO SUMMON
THE TRUE STRENGTH OF
THE SOMIN SHORAI.
- OH...
WAIT, SERIOUSLY?
- YEAH. ALSO, IF YOU WEAR THIS,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO INCREASE YOUR
SPIRIT POWER SIGNIFICANTLY.
- HUH.
- NOT ORDINARY CLOTHES, THIS IS
THE ATTIRE OF A PRIESTESS.
THE LINK BETWEEN GOD AND MAN.
- PRIESTESS?
I KINDA LIKE
WHERE YOU'RE GOING WITH THIS!
- ALTHOUGH, I HAVE
MODIFIED IT SOME.
- UH... WHAT IS THIS?
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
- ( crying loudly )
I WORKED THREE STRAIGHT
DAYS AND NIGHTS
TO MAKE IT, SWEET CHEEKS!
- THIS IS SACRILEGE!
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED!
- ALL IS READY, IT IS TIME,
ICHIKO SAKURA! NOW ATTACK HER!
- ( yelling )
THIS INDEED HAS A "THE BATTLE
BETWEEN GOD AND GIRL NOW BEGINS"
FEEL TO IT, DON'T YA THINK?
- WHAT'S WITH THIS MANGA
THAT'S BEEN CANCELED THING?
- WELL, WE'RE HALFWAY THROUGH
THE EPISODE, SO, I JUST...
- WHAT? ALREADY?
- ( groans )
( groans louder )
SO, WHICH DO YOU LIKE THE BEST?
( giggling )
WAY CUTE!
YOU'RE RIGHT. TOO SHORT.
THIS ONE'S NOT BAD. SO,
WHICH STYLE DO YOU LIKE BEST?
REALLY?
- GET YOUR BUTT OUT
HERE, POVERTY GOD!
TODAY IS THE DAY WE
SETTLE THIS FOR GOOD!
- ( yawns )
HUSH. KEEP IT DOWN. GOD!
( gasps )
WHOA! THAT OUTFIT,
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING IT FOR?
- SHE SNICKERED AT ME!
- IT'S JUST... LOOK AT YOU.
- YOU FOOL! IF YOU'RE
GONNA COSPLAY,
YOU CAN'T GO BREAKING
CHARACTER ALL OVER THE PLACE!
- THEN WHAT KIND OF CHARACTER
DESIGN IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE?
- Momiji: HEY! LOOK THIS WAY!
- ( camera clicking )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU CAN'T TAKE PICTURES
WITHOUT ASKING FIRST!
- THAT'S IT! I'M JOINING
THE NEWSPAPER CLUB.
- OH, NO! I DON'T THINK SO!
- Momiji: THE FRONT
PAGE IS ALL MINE!
SERIOUSLY, YOU'RE GOIN' ALL AGRO
ON ME FOR THAT?
LOVELY SOMIN SHORAI CHARM.
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK IT'LL HELP
YOU GET RID OF ME?
- HOW'D SHE KNOW?
- OH, I'M NOT ALL THAT
SURPRISED SHE FIGURED IT OUT.
SHE'S A GOD, YA DIG?
- ( chuckles )
NEVER MIND THAT.
( laughs )
THIS PICTURE IS AWESOME!
I WONDER WHAT ALL THE BOYS
IN CLASS ARE GONNA THINK
WHEN THEY GET A LOOK
AT THIS BAD BOY!
( laughs )
- I'M NOT DOING THIS
BECAUSE I WANT TO.
BUT THE MOMENT YOU GOT HERE,
EVERYTHING IN MY LIFE
STARTED GOING TO HELL,
AND I'M SICK OF IT.
THIS THING ENDS NOW! I WON'T LET
YOU SCREW UP MY LIFE ANYMORE!
( yells )
- YEAH! THE POWER IS
COMING FORTH!
- UM. WHAT IS THAT ALL ABOUT?
- OH. SO COOL. HEY, GUYS!
- I KNOW SHE'S NOT
A NORMAL HUMAN BEING
AND CAN'T REALLY HELP IT,
BUT THIS GIRL IS
A MAJOR FREAKIN' PAIN.
- YOUR TIME IS UP HERE, POVERTY
GOD. GET OUT OF MY HOUSE!
- DAMN! THAT WAS GONNA BE
MY FRONT PAGE SCOOP!
- ( growling )
- ( mooing )
- THESE GUYS MAY ALL
LOOK ADORABLE,
BUT THEY'RE ACTUALLY
PRETTY BRUTAL!
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE A REFLECTION
OF ICHIKO'S PERSONALITY.
- ( screaming )
- MOVE! DON'T LET
THE POVERTY GOD GET AWAY!
- GEEZ. THIS ISN'T
A FIGHTING SHOW. WHAT THE F?
( screaming )
- GOOD JOB,
WE'VE GOT HER CORNERED!
TAKE THIS!
TAKE THAT! AND THAT!
AND A LITTLE BIT OF THIS!
YOU LIKE THAT?
YOU READY TO REST IN PEACE?
- I DON'T LIKE ANY OF THIS!
KNOCK IT OFF ALREADY.
OR ELSE... I AM A GOD!
- WELL?
- GAH! YOU'RE SO ANNOYING.
THIS MAY BE A PAIN, BUT WHAT
ELSE CAN I DO? PREPARE YOURSELF.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET EFFED IN
THE A WITH A WHOLE BAG OF DS.
- UH. WHAT'S THAT?
- ENERGY. MINE THIS TIME.
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE THAT NAIVE.
DID IT NOT OCCUR TO YOU
I CAN DO ANYTHING YOU CAN DO?
GO! SHOW HER THE POWER
OF A POVERTY GOD!
LET HER FEEL YOUR CURSE!
- I'M NOT AFRAID OF YOU!
SO COME ON AND FEEL THE
PAIN, FANCY PANTS!
- UH, GO WHERE EXACTLY?
- UM, GUYS?
- ( gasps )
- LET'S JUST PRETEND
WE DIDN'T HEAR HER, OKAY?
- YEAH. THIS IS, LIKE,
TOTALLY LAME.
- Momiji: COME ON, YOU GUYS,
GIMME A BREAK.
- Fallen Warrior B: I DIDN'T
HEAR ANYTHING, DID YOU?
- Fallen Warrior A: YOU MEAN
LIKE A GOD TRYING TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF HER POWER?
- YOU ALL WANNA WATCH TV?
'CAUSE I DO.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- BASICALLY IT'S LIKE THIS...
DUE TO MY SPECIFIC PERSONALITY
I AM EASILY ANNOYED.
THESE FELLOWS, WHO WERE BORN
OF MY UNHAPPINESS ENERGY,
ARE EASILY ANNOYED BY THINGS,
TOO. AND THAT EXPLAINS THAT.
- OH... WELL, ISN'T THAT FUNNY?
- TIME OUT.
- Ichiko: OVERRULED!
I DID IT.
I WON.
ALTHOUGH, I DO GET THE FEELING
I MIGHT HAVE LOST A LITTLE, TOO.
( yelling ) EITHER WAY,
IN YOUR FACE, POVERTY GOD!
( laughing maniacally )
- Bobby: APPARENTLY,
SHE'S FORGOTTEN ALL ABOUT ME.
- Yamabuki: I SEE. SO WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING IS,
EVEN WHEN YOU WENT AT THIS HUMAN
WITH EVERYTHING YOU HAD,
YOU STILL FAILED TO BEAT HER.
THE SITUATION IS
ABUNDANTLY CLEAR.
I THINK WE SHOULD REEVALUATE.
I WANT YOU TO COME BACK
TO THE POVERTY GOD REALM
FOR NOW, MOMIJI.
- NO. PLEASE, LET ME TRY
ON MY OWN A LITTLE LONGER.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I JUST... THERE'S SOMETHING
IMPORTANT I...
THERE'S A THING I HAVE
CALLED MY PRIDE! YA FEEL ME, YO?
- WELL, ON THE PLUS SIDE,
I DON'T THINK SHE'S EVER
BEEN THIS MOTIVATED BEFORE.
- ( sighs )
WE START REFORMULATING
A STRATEGY TOMORROW.
THANK YOU AS ALWAYS.
( sobbing )
- Yamabuki: EVEN WHEN
YOU WENT AT THIS HUMAN
WITH EVERYTHING YOU HAD,
YOU STILL FAILED TO BEAT HER.
- BY A LITTLE GIRL. I'VE NEVER
BEEN SO HUMILIATED IN MY LIFE.
NO MATTER WHAT,
I WILL TAKE YOU OUT, ICHIKO.
YOU'RE SO GONNA REGRET
CROSSING ME.
- I MEAN, IT'S NICE THAT
THE POVERTY GOD IS GONE AND ALL,
BUT STILL, THIS SUCKS.
THINGS HAVE GONE FROM
BAD TO WORSE AND I BLAME YOU!
- NOT MY BAD.
- HOW CAN YOU NOT KNOW
HOW TO PUT THEM BACK?
- HEY, IF I DON'T KNOW,
I DON'T KNOW.
- Fallen Warrior B: HELLO!
YOU GOT ANY ICE SO I CAN
CHILL THIS BEER, MAN?
- EVERYONE, GET OUT OF HERE
RIGHT NOW!
- I'M HOME.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING WALKING
IN HERE LIKE IT WAS NORMAL?
GEEZ, I SWEAR, EVERY TIME
I SEE YOU IT'S JUST... I'M...
( screams )
- OKAY. I'VE COME UP WITH A WAY
TO CATCH ICHIKO OFF GUARD
AND IT'S GONNA BE LEGENDARY.
I FIGURE ANY GIRL AS STUBBORN
AS THAT PRINCESS
HAS TO BE SUPER INNOCENT
AND PURE ON THE INSIDE.
HEY, ICHIKO,
WANNA KNOW WHAT I HEARD?
SO, LIKE, THIS IS CRAZY,
BUT IT TURNS OUT BABIES
AREN'T ACTUALLY DELIVERED
BY STORKS AT ALL.
WHEN YOU'RE GIVEN A MERE
THREE-MONTH ANIME RUN,
YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO ROLL OVER
AND NOT TAKE THE INITIATIVE.
WITH THAT BEING UNDERSTOOD,
I'VE THOUGHT UP SOME IDEAS
FOR CHARACTER MERCHANDISE
TO INCREASE
OUR POPULARITY.
- ( groans )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS IS ICHIKO SAKURA'S
SPECIAL BOOBIE MOUSEPAD.
- WHAT? DON'T YOU THINK
THESE ARE PLAYED OUT?
I THINK THIS FLAT ONE
IS MORE NOVEL.
- A FIRST EVER EVEN SURFACED
POVERTY GOD MOUSE PAD
WITH NOT A SINGLE LADY LUMP!
- ( laughs )
WELL, SHOWS WHAT YOU KNOW.
THAT'S JUST A REGULAR BORING
MOUSE PAD, GENIUS.
- ( screaming )
- I'LL KILL YOU!
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
STARTED IT, JACKWAGON!
- Students: THIS WEEK'S...
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO!
SORRY TO KEEP YOU
WAITING, EVERYBODY.
DID YOU GET TO SEE MY TREMENDOUS
EXPLOITS THIS WEEK?
WELL, IF NOT, YOU'RE IN LUCK,
'CAUSE HERE IT IS ONE MORE TIME.
IT'S PRACTICALLY BRILLIANT,
IS IT NOT?
BUT HOLD ON, FOLKS,
THAT'S NOT ALL!
OH, WOW, LOOK AT
ME, A TWO IN ONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN TO QUIT!
I WONDER WHAT SURPRISES
I'LL HAVE IN STORE
FOR YOU NEXT TIME!
( laughing loudly )