- HEY, GOOD MORNING.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
( giggling )
- AND YOU ARE?
- WHO AM I?
IT'S MOMIJI, SILLY GIRL.
( giggling )
YOUR FRIENDLY NEIGHBORHOOD
POVERTY GOD.
- ( Ichiko screaming )
- Girl 1: HEY,
DID YOU SEE THAT GIRL?
- Girl 2: YEAH,
IT'S MOMIJI, RIGHT?
- Boy 1: IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
ANYTHING'S REALLY
CHANGED ABOUT HER.
- Boy 2: STILL, IT'S LIKE
SHE'S A DIFFERENT PERSON.
- HEADS UP.
( grunts )
( laughing )
- THERE'S NO WAY. I DON'T
BUY ANYTHING ABOUT THIS.
- WHAT DO I DO?
- UNLESS IT'S BECAUSE
I FORCED HER TO TAKE A BATH
IN THE LAST EPISODE.
YEAH, I BET SHE'S
TRYING TO CONVINCE ME
SHE'S CLEANED UP HER ACT.
( gasps ) KUMAGAI?
- Aw...
- HE'S SO CUTE. I WANT ONE!
- HE'S MOVING.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE.
- THAT LITTLE STUFFED
PUNK IS FAKING
THAT HE'S NOT AN ASS, TOO.
- I THOUGHT OF THE FISHERMEN...
THE BLACKBERRY PATCHES AND
THE BLUEBERRY HILLS.
- Kuramochi: MAN,
SHE IS SO COOL.
- Girl: SHE'S GOT
SUCH A PRETTY VOICE.
- ( Ichiko growling )
- DON'T LISTEN TO IT.
- CROWS ARE ALL LIARS.
- LOOK AT HER.
I NEVER REALIZED HOW
CUTE SHE WAS.
- I THINK I'M GOING TO START
TREATING HER DIFFERENTLY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING,
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO FORGET
ABOUT ICHIKO?
- YOU'RE A CHEATING
TRAITOR, DUDE!
- I DIDN'T SAY
I WAS GONNA SWITCH,
I JUST SAID I'LL BE NICER!
- WOULD YOU GUYS
TRY TO KEEP IT DOWN, PLEASE?
- WE'RE SORT OF IN
THE MIDDLE OF CLASS.
- NO ONE ASKED YOU,
SO SHUT THE HELL UP.
- HEY, CALM DOWN, PLEASE...
- DO YOU GIVE ANYONE WHO'S
NOT IN A BOY BAND A CHANCE?
- YEAH, WELL, WE WOULD
IF YOU GUYS EVER TALKED
ABOUT ANYONE BUT ICHIKO.
- BESIDES, RANMARU IS MORE MANLY
THAN ALL YOU LOSERS
PUT TOGETHER.
- WAIT, I'M WHAT?
- ENOUGH ALREADY.
KNOCK IT OFF.
- EVERYBODY STOP FIGHTING NOW!
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
BE RESPECTFUL OF THE TEACHER.
WE'RE IN HIGH-SCHOOL,
NOT KINDERGARTEN.
WE KINDA NEED TO START ACTING
LIKE ADULTS AT SOME POINT.
- OH, SORRY, MOMIJI.
- YEAH, WE DIDN'T MEAN
TO MAKE YOU ANGRY WITH US.
- WHO IS SHE TO TELL THEM
TO GROW UP?
- WE APOLOGIZE. PLEASE,
CONTINUE THE LESSON.
- I'VE WAITED ALL SEASON
AND NOBODY HAS EVER CARED
ABOUT HOW I FEEL UNTIL NOW.
( crying ) LOOK AWAY!
- DUDE, OUR TEACHER
TOTALLY JUST BAILED.
- GEE, I CAN'T IMAGINE
WHY HE WOULD DO THAT.
- IT'S BECAUSE
WE'RE TOO ROWDY.
- OR MAYBE IT'S JUST YOU.
- FINE. I WOULD LIKE
TO TAKE THIS MOMENT
TO HAVE A WORD WITH
ALL OF YOU BOYS.
- Boys: WHAT? US?
- I THINK IT'S WONDERFUL
THAT YOU'RE SO NICE TO ICHIKO
BUT YOU CAN'T ONLY EVER
BE NICE TO HER.
AS MEN, YOU SHOULD BE KIND
NOT JUST TO THOSE YOU LIKE.
INSTEAD, YOU HAVE TO
HAVE THE CAPACITY
TO SHARE YOUR KINDNESS
WITH EVERYBODY.
- Boys: WHOA! SHE'S SMART!
- SHE MAKES PEOPLE
UNHAPPY FOR A LIVING.
- IF YOU KEEP ACTING
THE WAY YOU'VE BEEN...
THERE'S NO WAY ANYONE
WILL THINK YOU'RE DATABLE.
- HECK, YEAH.
YOU TELL 'EM, MOMIJI.
- HOLD ON, IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU GIRLS HAVE ROOM TO JUDGE.
- Girls: HUH?
- EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU
TREATS RANMARU LIKE A BOY.
IN WHAT WORLD DO YOU THINK
A GIRL WANTS TO BE CALLED
BUTCH ALL THE TIME?
- Oh.
- WE, UH...
- MEH, I DON'T REALLY
MIND ALL THAT MUCH.
- BEHOLD, THE REAL RANMARU.
SEE, THIS IS THE KIND OF GIRL
SHE REALLY IS.
- HEY, WHAT IN GIRLY HELL
DID YOU DO TO ME?
- ( all gasping )
- THE POVERTY GOD ITEM,
"CHANGING RING," IS A DEVICE
THAT FACILITATES
COSPLAY IN AN INSTANT!
- HOWEVER, IT'S
LIMITED TO CLOTHING
THAT'S ALREADY BEEN WORN!
- OH, YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
- NO WAY! RANMARU?
- OH, UH, IT'S NO BIGGIE.
THANKS, THOUGH.
- SEE, TSUWABUKI?
SHE LOOKS CUTE, RIGHT?
- HUH?
YEAH. YEAH, SURE. WHY NOT?
I THINK YOU LOOK REALLY CUTE.
- ( exclaiming )
THIS IS TOO MUCH. IT'S TOO
MUCH. IT'S WAY TOO MUCH.
- NO, COME BACK, RANMARU.
- WHAT IS LIFE?
WHAT IS HAPPINESS?
- OH, NO. I THINK I MIGHT
HAVE GONE TOO FAR WITH HER.
- GEEZ, YOU THINK SO?
STUPID POVERTY GOD.
WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH HER NOW?
ANY IDEAS?
- ( mewing )
- ( giggling )
DID YOU HEAR?
HE SAID I WAS CUTE.
- GIRL, YOU HAVE GOT
TO SNAP OUT OF IT.
- I COULD DIE NOW. I COULD
DIE AND TOTALLY BE HAPPY.
- KNOWING THE POVERTY GOD,
THERE'S NO DOUBT SHE'S
UP TO SOMETHING.
MAYBE SHE'S TRYING TO GET THE
WHOLE CLASS TO LIKE HER
MORE THAN ME? BUT WHY?
- I'M HOME.
OH. RANMARU, I DIDN'T
KNOW YOU'D BE HERE.
OKAY, CHECK THIS OUT.
THEY WERE HAVING AN EVENT, SO
I GOT THE MEAT FOR HALF OFF.
AND NOW THAT RANMARU IS HERE,
I'LL MAKE SOMETHING EXTRA
SPECIAL FOR US.
- YOU'VE GOT SOME NERVE.
HOW DARE YOU THINK YOU CAN
JUST WALTZ INTO MY HOUSE
LIKE IT WAS NOTHING.
AND ARE YOU WEARING
MY UNIFORM, TOO?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS
GOOD GIRL ACT IS ALL ABOUT,
BUT I WISH YOU'D KNOCK IT OFF
BECAUSE IT'S STARTING
TO ANNOY ME.
- GOOD GIRL ACT?
- YOU HEARD ME.
- ( gasps )
- I'M SO SORRY. I COMPLETELY
FORGOT TO TELL YOU.
- HUH?
- CRAZY THINGS CAN
HAPPEN TO POVERTY GODS
AND THEIR FAMILIARS,
LIKE KUMAGAI.
FOR EXAMPLE, IF WE'RE WASHED
WHILE IN THE HUMAN REALM,
WE RANDOMLY LOSE ALL OF OUR
POVERTY GOD POWERS,
WHICH IS WEIRD, YEAH?
- YEAH.
- AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS
OUR PERSONALITIES CHANGE, TOO.
- THEY WHAT?
- THIS IS THE RESULT.
SO LET'S TRY TO GET ALONG
FROM NOW ON, OKAY?
- AW, SHE'S SWEET.
- ( growling )
- ( humming )
- HER PERSONALITY CHANGES IF SHE
LOSES HER POVERTY GOD POWERS?
FOR REAL?
BECAUSE THIS SOUNDS A LOT
LIKE ANOTHER ONE OF HER SCHEMES.
OF COURSE, THAT'S IT! I TOTALLY
KNOW WHAT SHE'S UP TO THIS TIME!
SHE HAS TO BE
TRYING TO CONVINCE ME
THAT SHE'S SOME
SUPER NICE GIRL NOW,
SO THAT I'LL DROP MY
GUARD AROUND HER.
THEN, SHE'LL WAIT
UNTIL THE RIGHT TIME
TO CATCH ME BY SURPRISE AND
TAKE MY HAPPINESS ENERGY AWAY.
- Momiji: ICHIKO.
- DO YOU THINK I'M GONNA TAKE
YOUR HAPPINESS ENERGY AWAY?
BE HONEST, PLEASE... IS THAT
THE KIND OF PERSON I LOOK LIKE?
- YES IT IS.
FOR SURE.
YOU'RE PLANNING TO
SHOW YOUR TRUE COLORS
RIGHT WHEN I LEAST EXPECT
IT, AREN'T YOU?
THE WHOLE THING IS
JUST FOR SHOW...
I KNOW THAT LOOK YOU GET
WHEN YOU THINK YOU'VE WON.
SUWANO...
- ICHIKO!
- I KNEW IT.
I WAS RIGHT ABOUT YOU,
POVERTY GOD...
HE WHO ATTACKS FIRST
ALWAYS WINS.
- Ranmaru: HEY, ICHIKO!
- Ichiko: I KNEW IT!
NO WAY SHE'S NOT
TRYING TO TRICK ME.
- THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
I CAN DO.
- HUH?
- AND AS MUCH AS I'D
RATHER SHOOT MYSELF IN THE FACE,
I'M CALLING IN THE BOYS.
- OH, HEY, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU GUYS WERE COMING, TOO.
BUT THAT'S OKAY, I MADE TOO MUCH
SO THERE'S ENOUGH FOR EVERYONE.
WHO'S HUNGRY?
- THAT IS NOT HER. THAT
PERSON IS NOT MY MOMIJI.
IT'S NOT, IT'S NOT HER.
- WAIT A MINUTE, YOU DIDN'T
KNOW SHE WAS ACTING LIKE THIS?
- IF YOU ASK ME,
SHE LOOKS CUTER THIS WAY.
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT US TO DO
ABOUT HER BEING SO NICE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
RIGHT NOW SHE'S SAYING SHE
LOST HER POVERTY GOD POWERS
ON TOP OF HER LITTLE
BIPOLAR SWITCHEROO.
BUT I THINK THIS
IS JUST AN ACT
SO SHE CAN STEAL MY
HAPPINESS ENERGY AGAIN.
AND THAT IS WHY I WANT YOU
TO USE YOUR PERVERSION POWER,
GRAB THAT MASK SHE'S PUT ON
AND SHRED IT FROM HER FACE.
- Both: OH!
- I CAN GET BEHIND THAT.
- AND I WOULD DO ANYTHING
TO GET MY MOMIJI TO TURN BACK
INTO HER NORMAL SELF.
- ALL RIGHT, ALLOW ME TO
START BY GIVING HER
WHAT WE IN PROFESSIONAL CIRCLES
LIKE TO CALL, THE SHOCK THERAPY.
- WHAT'S THE SHOCK THERAPY?
- ( gasps )
- Bobby: TITTIES.
- WHY, YOU FILTHY MONK,
YOU'RE NOT ONLY TRYING
TO SINK YOUR DISGUSTING
FANGS INTO ICHIKO,
NOW YOU'RE GONNA GO
AFTER MOMIJI, TOO.
- I'LL ALLOW IT.
GO FOR IT, MY PERVERTED WARRIOR.
- GUESS WHO.
- OH, WELL, LET ME THINK
ABOUT IT. IT'S BOBBY, RIGHT?
( giggling ) YOU'RE SILLY.
- OH, YEAH, I GUESS
I GAVE MYSELF AWAY.
- TELL ME WHAT THE HELL
WAS SO SHOCKING ABOUT THAT?
- I'M SORRY, BABY. THERE WAS
NOWHERE FOR MY HANDS TO LAND!
- AND BESIDES,
HER AURA IS WAY TOO PURE.
I COULD NEVER INTENTIONALLY
GROPE A LADY LIKE THAT.
- WAIT, DON'T TELL ME
HE FEELS GUILTY.
- HEY! WHAT ABOUT ME, YOU JERK?
YOU TRY TO GROPE
ME ALL THE TIME.
- IF I'M NOT PURE, WHAT AM I?
- A BITCH.
- GUYS, ENOUGH WHINING,
IT'S TIME TO ACT. I'LL GO NEXT.
THE GOAL IS TO GET MOMIJI TO
TURN BACK INTO HER NORMAL SELF,
RIGHT?
- CORRECT. PLEASE TELL ME
YOU HAVE A WAY TO DO THAT.
- TRUST HER. IF YOU
KEEP BELIEVING IN HER
AND PRAYING DEEP
DOWN IN YOUR HEART
THAT MOMIJI WILL RETURN
TO HER NORMAL SELF, SOMEDAY,
I KNOW IT WILL COME TRUE.
- WHY I THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT ACTUALLY HAVE
A LOGICAL ANSWER IS BEYOND ME.
- JOIN THE CIRCLE.
- ( groans )
- ALL RIGHT, AS MOMIJI'S
NUMBER ONE SERVANT,
I'M UP FOR WHATEVER
MIGHT FIX HER.
- MOMO'O.
- HUH?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU KEEP
DOING THIS TO YOURSELF.
YOU POOR BABY,
YOU'RE ALL BRUISED.
WHEN YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH YOU HAVE
TO SAY THAT YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH.
- UH, I DO WHAT?
- ( blowing air )
OWIE, OWIE GO AWAY. DON'T COME
BACK SOME OTHER DAY.
- YOUR WARMTH IS TERRIFYING.
- ( scoffs )
- THE MASOCHIST IS UNABLE TO
TOLERATE WARMTH AND KINDNESS.
- WHY DID YOU HAVE TO GO
AND BREAK A WINDOW?
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF FOOD,
SO EAT UP!
- AWESOME! IT LOOKS SO GOOD!
- THAT IS TIGHT.
- Momiji: WHAT DO WE SAY
BEFORE A MEAL?
- THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD.
- Ranmaru: AREN'T YOU
TWO GONNA EAT?
- NO, I'M NOT GONNA EAT. THANK
YOU, THOUGH, YOU BIG TRAITOR.
- OH, COME ON, SHE WENT THROUGH
ALL THE TROUBLE TO MAKE IT.
CAN'T WE TURN HER BACK
AFTER WE PIG OUT?
- PLUS, WOULDN'T IT MAKE
MORE SENSE NOT TO CHANGE HER
SO GOOD MOMIJI CAN STICK AROUND?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- NOT YOU TOO, TAMA!
- WELL, IF YOU DON'T
WANT TO JOIN US,
I'LL BRING THIS OVER HERE
SINCE I MADE IT JUST FOR YOU.
- NO, I'M FINE. WILL YOU
ANSWER A QUESTION, THOUGH?
IF YOU DON'T HAVE YOUR SPECIAL
POVERTY GOD POWERS,
AND YOU'RE NOT A POVERTY
GOD ANYMORE,
THEN YOU REALLY HAVE NO REASON
TO HANG AROUND ME, DO YOU?
- NO, THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
I MAY NOT HAVE POWERS,
BUT I STILL HAVE MY
POVERTY GOD MISSION.
- WHAT'S THE MISSION NOW?
I DON'T ABSORB OTHER
PEOPLE'S HAPPINESS.
SO WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL? I'VE GOT
THIS FANCY KEYSTONE FOR THAT.
- YOU DID PUT IT ON YOURSELF,
WHICH IS GREAT,
BUT I AM STILL SUPPOSED
TO TAKE BACK
YOUR EXTRA HAPPINESS ENERGY.
THE TIME HAS COME TO PAY ALL
THAT GOOD FORTUNE FORWARD
AND HELP OTHER PEOPLE,
THAT IS YOUR GIFT.
- CAN I GET A RECEIPT,
I'D LIKE TO RETURN IT?
- JUST WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE HOW
WONDERFUL YOU FEEL.
- NO WAY.
- I PROMISE YOUR HEART
WILL NEVER BE THE SAME.
I THINK WE CAN DO
THIS THING TOGETHER.
- WHY WOULD I WANNA DO
ANYTHING WITH YOU?
- OKAY, SO MAYBE WE'LL
TAKE A LITTLE BREAK FOR NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY THIS
AND SEE IF YOU LIKE IT?
DO YOU EVER LISTEN?
I SAID I DON'T WANT ANY!
- All: HMM?
- UH.
- ( sobbing )
- MOMIJI, WAIT.
- Bobby: DAMN, GIRL,
TALK ABOUT COLD-BLOODED.
- Momo'o: THAT WAS UNCALLED FOR.
- WHAT, SO NOW
SHE'S ALL SENSITIVE?
- ICHIKO. GO AFTER HER!
GET YOUR BUTT MOVING!
- WHAT IS GOING ON?
WHY IS RANMARU
SO MAD AT ME ALL OF A SUDDEN?
WHY?
AND WHY DO I HAVE TO BE THE ONE
TO CHASE DOWN THE POVERTY GOD?
HEY, POVERTY GOD.
- ICHIKO.
- UH... DO... UM...
YOU WANNA GO HOME?
- ARE YOU SURE?
- DON'T GET THE WRONG IDEA.
I MEAN I'M ONLY HERE
BECAUSE RANMARU YELLED AT ME.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M DYING TO BE
BESTIES WITH YOU OR ANYTHING.
- YES, I UNDERSTAND.
- TELL ME THE TRUTH. WHAT
EXACTLY IS THE DEAL WITH YOU?
YOU SHOW UP OUT OF NOWHERE,
TOTALLY SCREW UP MY LIFE
WHEN AND WHEREVER YOU CAN,
AND NOW, FOR SOME UNKNOWN
REASON, YOU WANT TO BE FRIENDS.
HOW MUCH ARE YOU PLANNING
TO JERK ME AROUND?
- I'M SO SORRY.
- NO, DON'T APOLOGIZE.
THAT JUST PISSES ME OFF
EVEN MORE.
- I JUST... I WANT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND SOMETHING.
MY OTHER SELF, NOT ME RIGHT NOW,
BUT THE MOMIJI YOU'RE
USED TO SEEING,
WELL, BOTH OF US, I GUESS,
WE DON'T WANT ANY UNHAPPINESS
TO COME TO YOU. IT'S THE TRUTH.
- NO, IT'S NOT. YOU'RE
ALWAYS TALKING ABOUT
TAKING AWAY MY
HAPPINESS ENERGY.
DOING THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT WILL
MAKE UNHAPPINESS COME TO ME.
- FORCIBLY STEALING THE ENERGY
ISN'T THE ONLY WAY TO
REDUCE YOUR LEVEL.
- I ASSUME YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
THE PATTERN WE SET UP
WHERE I GIVE IT AWAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU
WON'T GIVE UP ON THAT.
I NEVER SAID I WAS
PLANNING ON BECOMING A SAINT.
SO, ONE MORE TIME, SUWANO
AND RANMARU NOW I GUESS,
ARE THE ONLY PEOPLE
I CARE ABOUT.
EVERYONE ELSE CAN SUCK IT.
- WHEN WE FIRST MET,
IT WAS JUST MR SUWANO.
SEE? THAT'S HOW IT WORKS.
YOU SHARE GOOD FORTUNE, BUT YOU
DON'T LOSE ANYTHING.
OF COURSE, I'M NOT SAYING
YOU HAVE TO SUDDENLY
MAKE A HUNDRED FRIENDS.
LITTLE BY LITTLE IS FINE.
LITTLE BY LITTLE.
THE MORE PEOPLE YOU ALLOW
YOURSELF TO CARE ABOUT,
THE MORE HAPPINESS WILL
BE WAITING OUT THERE
FOR YOU TO FIND.
- WAIT, CALM DOWN.
- REMEMBER. YOU ONLY GET
BACK AS MUCH HAPPINESS
AS YOU ALLOW YOURSELF TO GIVE.
- YEAH, FINE. I GET THE POINT.
YOU CAN LAY OFF NOW.
IT'S POURING, SO IT
DOESN'T REALLY MATTER ANYWAY.
LOOK, CAN WE JUST GO?
I DON'T LIKE IT WHEN RANMARU
GETS ALL MAD AT ME.
- HEY, WELCOME BACK.
- GOOD, WE MADE IT.
- I HAD A FEELING
YOU GUYS WOULD BE SOAKED.
I GOT A BATH READY FOR YOU.
SORRY I DIDN'T ASK
YOU IF I COULD
MESS WITH YOUR
STUFF BEFORE I DID.
- OH, NO. IT'S FINE.
THANKS FOR THINKING AHEAD.
WAIT. UH, BATH TIME IS ME TIME.
- WHAT? SO MOMIJI'S JUST
SUPPOSED TO CATCH A COLD
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO SELFISH
TO SHARE YOUR BATH WITH HER?
- WHY DOES IT HAVE TO BE
AT THE SAME TIME?
- COME ON, WE CAN WASH
EACH OTHER'S BACKS.
- NO WAY!
IF YOU DECIDE TO ATTACK ME NOW,
I WILL KILL YOU.
- NO, I WON'T. I PROMISE.
SO LISTEN, ICHIKO, TO PICK BACK
UP WHERE WE LEFT OFF EARLIER...
- OH, YOU MEAN LIKE
THE PEOPLE I CARE ABOUT?
I THOUGHT WE WERE
DONE WITH THAT.
- NO, NOT QUITE YET.
ONCE YOU HAVE A LOT OF PEOPLE
YOU CARE FOR,
AND EVERYONE'S
SURROUNDING YOU, RIGHT?
IF I'M STANDING THERE NEXT TO
YOU, BY CHANCE, DO YOU,
ONE DAY, ANY DAY
WOULD BE FINE...
SORRY, THIS IS
EMBARRASSING, BUT...
I JUST HOPE SOMETIME
YOU'LL CALL ME BY MY NAME, TOO.
- I, UH...
THAT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN,
POVERTY GOD!
- ICHIKO'S YELLING AT ME AGAIN!
- KNOCK IT OFF!
- AFTER THAT THE POVERTY GOD
NEVER SHOWED ANY SIGNS
SHE'D TURN BACK TO
HER OTHER SELF.
LUCKY FOR ME, I STOPPED GETTING
ATTACKED ALL THE TIME, TOO.
MY DAILY LIFE SLOWLY WENT
BACK TO WHAT IT WAS
BEFORE SHE SHOWED UP.
I DON'T KNOW. SOMETHING SEEMED
KIND OF OFF, THOUGH.
A NORMAL ROUTINE IS NICE,
BUT I GUESS THERE WAS JUST
SOMETHING MISSING.
IT LEFT ME WITH
A WEIRD FEELING.
AND FOR WHATEVER REASON,
I CAN'T SHAKE IT.
- I WONDER IF IT
BOTHERS ICHIKO, TOO.
I HOPE IT'S NOT GOING TO
BE LIKE THIS FOREVER.
I WANT THE REAL MOMIJI BACK.
- ( mewing )
- YOU'RE KICKING IT TOO HARD!
- SORRY, RYU!
- OH, NO. I SURE HOPE
IT DIDN'T HIT ANYTHING.
- ( mewing )
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- MAN, THIS KITTEN
ISN'T TOO SMART
IF HE KEEPS TRYING TO JUMP
INTO THE BACK OF THE TRUCK.
- OH, I BET THE THING'S JUST
HUNGRY AND WANTS A SNACK.
- ( rattling )
- ( gasps )
( screaming )
NO! GARBAGE MONSTER!
- HUH?
- ( snarling )
( gasps ) KUMAGAI, YOU'RE BACK.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU, MAN.
HOW DID YOU SWING THE CHANGE?
THAT'S IT? YOU MEAN...
HECK YEAH, WE CAN!
- HEY, ICHIKO.
- ARE YOU READY TO GO HOME, NOW?
- DO YOU GUYS MIND
IF I COME OVER AND HANG OUT?
- NOT AT ALL. IN FACT, I THINK
I SHOULD MAKE A CAKE FOR US.
- THOSE THREE HAVE GOTTEN
PRETTY CLOSE, HUH?
- I WONDER HOW CLOSE IS CLOSE.
- ( yawning )
- Ranmaru: DAMN, ICHIKO.
MOVE IT OR LOSE IT.
- Momiji: OKAY, I FINISHED
WASHING THE DISHES.
NEXT UP ARE THE BATHTUB
AND THEN THE TOILET.
( humming )
- ( mewing )
- WHAT'S WRONG, TAMA?
- CRASHING THROUGH
THE WINDOW TIME. TA-DA.
- ( screams )
- PLEASE FORGIVE MY RUDENESS
BUT I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
- LET HER GO.
HEY! KNOCK IT OFF.
( grunting )
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
KUMAGAI? WAIT, HOW'D HE
GET BACK TO NORMAL?
MOMO'O, A LITTLE EXPLANATION
WOULD BE GREAT.
- I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T WANNA
BE SO ROUGH, FOR ONCE.
BUT I NEEDED TO
FIND MOMIJI FAST
SO I CAN TURN HER BACK INTO
A POVERTY GOD.
- WAIT, SERIOUSLY?
OKAY, BUT HOW?
( screaming )
WHY ARE YOU DOING THAT HERE?
SHE JUST CLEANED UP, TOO!
- NO, MY SOMIN SHORAI!
- WAIT, MOMO'O.
PLEASE. I WON'T RUN AWAY,
JUST PUT ME DOWN.
I WANT... I'D REALLY LIKE
TO SAY GOODBYE TO ICHIKO.
- OKAY, SURE.
- SO THIS IS MORE THAN LIKELY
THE LAST TIME I'LL EVER BE ABLE
TO TAKE ON MY MIRROR FORM.
UNFORTUNATELY, I'M
AFRAID THE OTHER MOMIJI
DOESN'T THINK TOO HIGHLY OF ME.
I KNOW IT HASN'T LASTED LONG
BUT I HAVE ENJOYED IT.
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I REALLY DID WANT TO BE
FRIENDS WITH YOU.
GOODBYE, SWEET ICHIKO.
BE NICE TO THE OTHER
MOMIJI FOR ME.
- WAIT.
POVERTY GOD.
- EXCUSE ME BOSS.
THERE'S A REAL LIVE MONK
HERE WHO'S SAYING
HE COULD USE SOME
PART TIME WORK.
- HUH? LET'S SEE.
WELL, DOES HE HAVE A LICENSE?
IF HE CAN DRIVE A CAR, I GUESS
IT'LL MAKE DOING THE
DRINK DELIVERIES
A LITTLE EASIER ON YOU.
I CAN'T IMAGINE IT'S
TOO MUCH FUN FOR YOU
TO DO ON YOUR BIKE
ALL NIGHT LONG.
- DO YOU HAVE A LICENSE?
- SURE, I'VE GOT ONE.
BOBBY MCLOVIN, THAT'S ME.
- OKAY, IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND.
- WHOA, HOLD ON.
LET'S ROLL OUT.
- Students: THIS WEEK'S...
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO!
- WHAT? THE NEXT EPISODE
IS THE LAST ONE?
OH, WOW. OKAY SHINOBU,
THERE'LL BE NO MORE DAWDLING
AROUND, YOU HEAR ME?
IF THEY'RE NOT GOING TO GIVE ME
ANY EXTRA APPEARANCES,
THEN I'M JUST GOING TO
HAVE TO STEAL THEM.
NEXT WEEK I'LL SHOW THEM WHAT
THEY'VE BEEN MISSING OUT ON!