- ( sighs )
- Kakashi: WELL, IF IT ISN'T
MY FRIEND URASHIMAKO.
WHY THE LONG SIGH, AND IN
SUCH A DRAMATIC FASHION?
- OH, HEY, SORRY,
IT'S JUST MOMIJI AGAIN.
- MOMIJI, HUH? YOU MEAN THAT
POVERTY GOD WHO GETS HER KICKS
FROM WORKING YOU
LIKE A SLAVE, RIGHT?
- THAT'S HER. SHE WAS TRYING TO
STEAL THE HAPPINESS ENERGY
FROM A HUMAN NAMED ICHIKO SAKURA
USING THE PRINCESS'S
TREASURE BOX
TO TURN HER INTO AN OLD WOMAN,
BUT BECAUSE I MESSED UP, SHE GOT
TURNED INTO A CHILD INSTEAD.
ICHIKO GOT AWAY AND
HID OUT IN THE HOUSE
OF ONE OF HER CLASSMATES,
TSUWABUKI,
AND WHILE MOMIJI LOOKED FOR HER,
SHE TOLD ME TO GET MORE
TREASURE BOXES SO,
SHE COULD TURN THE GIRL INTO
AN OLD WOMAN LIKE SHE'D PLANNED.
THEN MOMIJI WENT ON A PICNIC
AND SEEMS TO HAVE CAUGHT
ICHIKO, BUT NOW,
SHE'S WAITING ON ME TO GET HER
THOSE TREASURE BOXES.
EVERYONE'S BEEN WORKING ME
REALLY HARD, AND I'M EXHAUSTED.
HENCE THE SIGHING IN
A DRAMATIC FASHION.
EVEN NOW, THEY'RE
MAKING ME SUBTLY RECAP
THE LAST EPISODE'S PLOT.
- YEAH, THAT WAS
NOT AT ALL SUBTLE.
- HEY, MICHIKO.
THAT'S NOT A GOOD SIGN. TELL
ME SHE DIDN'T FALL DOWN THERE.
OH NO.
( screaming )
- ( giggling )
- ( leaves rustling )
- Ichiko: I CAN'T BELIEVE
I GOT AWAY.
- MICHIKO.
- RIKA, HEY. HOW'S IT GOIN'?
- THANK GOODNESS. YOU SEEM OKAY.
GOOD. UM, WHERE'S KEITA?
IS HE NOT WITH YOU?
- HUH?
- IF NOT, THEN WHERE IS HE?
- Tsuwabuki: OH MAN, THAT HURTS.
NOW THAT'S WHAT I
WOULD CALL A CRAZY FALL.
IT'S A MIRACLE I EVEN SURVIVED
TO HURT THIS BADLY.
AW, NOT GOOD. I NEED TO
HURRY UP, FIND MICHIKO,
AND GET BACK TO EVERYONE
ELSE, BUT HOW?
I CAN'T MISS WORK TOMORROW.
NOT AGAIN.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
THERE AREN'T ANY MORE BUSES
UNTIL TOMORROW MORNING.
- I'M SURE. WE'LL WAIT HERE
UNTIL MY BROTHER COMES BACK.
- Mika: THINK HE'S OKAY?
- OF COURSE, HE'S
PERFECTLY FINE.
HE'LL BE BACK SOON AND
WE'LL BE FINE TOO.
WE JUST CAN'T LEAVE HIM OUT HERE
BY HIMSELF OR HE'D GET LONELY.
- I GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE.
- GEEZ, WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
TSUWABUKI? COME ON.
YOU'VE GOTTA GET BACK HERE
BEFORE THEY ALL LOSE IT.
- NO. SOMETHING'S WRONG.
I CAN JUST FEEL IT.
- NO. MIKA.
- IT'S TRUE. HE'S GONE.
HE'S GONE, AND HE'S GONNA
BE GONE FOREVER.
MOM AND DAD NEVER CAME BACK.
AND KEITA'S NEVER COMING
BACK, EITHER.
- SHUT UP, DON'T SAY STUFF
LIKE THAT. IT'S NOT TRUE.
HE'D NEVER LEAVE
US LIKE THEY DID.
HE'S COMING BACK.
STOP. YOU'RE MAKING SORATA CRY.
- RYU, THAT'S ENOUGH.
- PLEASE STOP CRYING. STOP.
- YOU CAN'T TELL THEM TO STOP
CRYING IF YOU'RE GONNA CRY, TOO.
PLEASE, THERE'S NOTHING
TO CRY ABOUT AT ALL.
- ( all crying )
- PLEASE, COME BACK. COME HOME.
- MICHIKO, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'M GONNA GO BACK OUT THERE
AND FIND YOUR BROTHER.
- YOU CAN'T.
WE WOULDN'T WANT YOU TO
WIND UP GETTING LOST, TOO.
- I'LL BE FINE.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT. YOU AND
THE KIDS JUST WAIT HERE.
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL BE ABLE TO FIND HIM.
TRUST ME.
I'LL GO FIND YOUR BROTHER
AND BRING HIM BACK TO YOU.
- MICHIKO, WAIT. OH.
GREAT. WHAT AM I GONNA DO NOW?
I HOPE SHE'S RIGHT.
- COME ON, WHERE
THE HECK DID HE GO?
- WE ARE ON IT, NOW. TAKE THIS.
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS, FEEL
FREE TO CALL ME.
- OKAY. WORTH A SHOT.
- ( howling )
- YOU SUMMON, AND I APPEAR.
YOU CALLED ME?
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
- I NEED TO USE YOUR NOSE.
I'M TRYING TO FIND THE
OWNER OF THIS HANKY,
HE'S LOST SOMEWHERE
ON THE MOUNTAIN.
- BUT, UH...
THIS SMELLS LIKE A DUDE.
- CAN YOU DO THIS FOR ME OR NOT?
- HECK YEAH. PIECE OF CAKE.
- I GET IT. I KNOW WHY I FEEL
SO AWKWARD AROUND THEM.
I HATE TO ADMIT IT.
BUT GOOD FOOD, MONEY, AND A BIG
HOUSE DON'T REALLY MATTER.
THERE ARE TONS OF
THINGS THAT I HAVE
AND CAN HAVE THAT
THEY NEVER WILL.
BUT... BUT EVERYTHING THAT I
DON'T HAVE, THEY DO!
IT ALL MAKES PERFECT
SENSE TO ME NOW.
PLEASE, MOMO'O, YOU
HAVE TO FIND HIM.
- ( chirping )
- ( barking )
- WELL? DID YOU
FIND HIM YET? TSUWABUKI!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
ALL THE WAY DOWN HERE?
ARE YOU AN IDIOT?
YOU'RE ABOUT TO DIE
AND YOU'RE JUST LAYING
AROUND LIKE A MORON.
GAH! COME ON, WAKE UP.
I SAID WAKE UP.
YOUR BROTHERS AND SISTERS
ARE WAITING FOR YOU.
THEY'RE CRYING
LIKE CRAZY PEOPLE,
AND IT'S REALLY ANNOYING.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO
THOSE KIDS IF YOU DON'T GO BACK?
I HOPE YOU'VE TAUGHT THEM WELL,
BECAUSE I'M NOT ABOUT TO TAKE
CARE OF THEM FOR YOU.
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
OPEN YOUR EYES. YOU HAVE TO.
OPEN YOUR EYES, RIGHT NOW!
( screaming )
- GIRL, YOU NEED TO
GET IT TOGETHER.
YOU LEFT YOURSELF WIDE OPEN.
WHAT ELSE COULD I DO?
- IS THAT SERIOUSLY ALL
YOU CAN THINK ABOUT?
- THANKS TO YOU,
I DIDN'T HAVE MUCH MONEY AND
COULD ONLY AFFORD TO BUY
THE SMALLEST SIZE
CAPSULE AVAILABLE.
BUT STILL, THERE SHOULD BE
ENOUGH IN THERE TO SAVE AT LEAST
ONE PERSON ON
THE VERGE OF DEATH.
- BUT POVERTY GOD.
- YES. I AM A POVERTY GOD,
NOT A GRIM REAPER,
SO IF SOMEONE INNOCENT WERE TO
DIE WHILE I WAS IN THE PROCESS
OF TAKING YOUR HAPPINESS ENERGY
THEY'D DO MORE
THAN JUST FIRE ME.
- BUT AREN'T YOU'RE
ALWAYS TALKING ABOUT
HOW YOU'RE GOING TO KILL ME?
- WELL, YEAH, BUT Y'KNOW,
FROM THE GREATEST HATE SPRINGS
FORTH THE GREATEST YADA - YADA.
YOU HAVE TO CONSIDER, THOUGH.
IF YOU DECIDE TO ALLOW
TSUWABUKI TO DIE,
IT WILL GUARANTEE I'LL
BE SENT AWAY,
OUT OF THE HUMAN REALM TO
SUFFER THE CONSEQUENCES
FOR HIS UNTIMELY DEATH.
- ( glass shattering )
- GOOD CHOICE. AW, HOW SWEET.
TO THINK THIS COULD HAVE BEEN
YOUR ONE AND ONLY CHANCE
TO GET RID OF ME.
- BELIEVE IT OR NOT, YOU DON'T
REALLY SCARE ME THAT MUCH.
IT'S JUST, IF HE
WERE TO DIE NOW,
I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
SLEEP AT NIGHT.
- ( chuckles )
- I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT.
HUMANITY'S A "B," HUH?
- WHOA, WHAT HAPPENED?
HOW IS IT ALREADY MORNING?
MICHIKO. I GUESS SHE MUST'VE
ENDED UP COMING TO LOOK FOR ME.
HOLD ON, IT'S NOT BROKEN.
AND MY HEAD ISN'T CUT ANYMORE.
DID I DREAM THE WHOLE THING UP?
ALL RIGHT, IT'S TIME
TO GO HOME NOW.
ALTHOUGH, I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE
HOW WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GET THERE.
HM. I DON'T REMEMBER THAT.
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN OVERNIGHT?
WELL, TIME TO FOLLOW
THE YELLOW BRICK ROAD, I GUESS.
AWESOME, I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
WAS REALLY THE RIGHT WAY.
- ( exclaiming )
- I'M BACK. SORRY
I'M SO LATE, YOU GUYS.
- KEITA.
- YOU'RE BACK.
- ( all crying )
- AW, MAN. WE HAVEN'T FOUND
A SINGLE THING YET, HAVE WE?
THAT NOSE OF YOURS AIN'T AS
RELIABLE AS YOU SAID IT WAS.
IT DIDN'T HELP THAT YOU
DISAPPEARED YESTERDAY
AND RUINED THE SEARCH, EITHER.
- I TOLD YOU ALREADY, ICHIKO
SUMMONED ME AND NEEDED HELP,
NOT THAT WE WOULD HAVE
GOTTEN ANYWHERE
WITH YOUR INCESSANT FLIRTING
WITH EVERY GIRL THAT YOU SEE.
ALTHOUGH, I AM DETECTING
A NEWER ODOR I DIDN'T SMELL
BEFORE THIS MORNING.
BASED ON THE SCENT,
AN URASHIMA TARO DEITY
HAS TO BE SOMEWHERE
NEARBY RIGHT NOW.
- ( man crying )
- WHAT'S WITH THIS IDIOT,
HE LOOKS RIDICULOUS.
- WHY DON'T YOU SHUT UP ABOUT
TURTLES AND GODS AND STUFF
AND GET YOUR ASS UP.
- I WON'T BE ABLE TO GET UP IF
YOU KEEP ROLLING ME ON MY BACK.
- ( together ) WE FINALLY
FOUND HIM!
GET OUT OF HERE BEFORE
I GIVE YOU SOMETHING
TO FLIP A TURTLE ABOUT!
- OH, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, KIND SIRS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I CAN
EVER REPAY YOU.
- I DO. HOW ABOUT YOU HAND OVER
THE TREASURE BOX, NOW.
- WAH. THINGS HAVE GONE
FROM BAD TO WORSE.
- HELLO THERE, LOVELY LADIES...
- HEY, ICHIKO. OVER HERE.
- MOMO'O. WHAT IS IT?
- GOOD NEWS. YOU DON'T
HAVE TO STAY A KID ANYMORE,
WE FOUND THE TREASURE BOX.
- YOU DID?
- HEY, MICHIKO, WE'RE LEAVING.
ARE YOU READY?
- YEAH, LET'S GO. OKAY,
I CAN'T DO THIS NOW,
SO I'LL HAVE TO FIND
YOU A LITTLE LATER.
- HEY, MICHIKO, HOW LONG DO YOU
THINK YOU'LL STAY WITH US?
- ( chuckles ) SO, THEY WANT ME
OUT OF THEIR HOUSE, HUH?
NEVER FEAR, I'LL BE OUT OF THERE
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
- WE LOVE HAVING YOU,
SO FEEL FREE TO STAY
AS LONG AS YOU WANT TO.
- HUH?
- AFTER ALL, YOU DID BRING
OUR BROTHER BACK TO US SAFELY.
I HAVE A GOOD FEELING ABOUT YOU.
YOU MIGHT JUST BE
OUR VERY OWN ANGEL,
SENT FROM HEAVEN TO BLESS US.
- HUH?
THE CRAP ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- OH, WOW. EVERYTHING I DON'T
HAVE IS HERE IN THIS HOME.
I CAN SEE THAT.
BUT SO WHAT.
IS THAT WHAT I WANT?
( laughs ) OF COURSE IT'S NOT.
WHY WOULD I, THE
ABNORMALLY LUCKY GIRL,
BE JEALOUS OF ANYONE ELSE? I
MEAN, SUPPOSE...
SUPPOSING, THIS...
AND THAT'S ALL I'M DOING HERE,
IS SUPPOSING.
BUT IF THIS WAS
SOMETHING I WANTED
AND IF I HAD TO KEEP LIVING
THIS WAY TO GET IT...
WOULD I?
IN REALITY, I'M STILL
ICHIKO SAKURA. I'M SORRY.
THERE IS NO MICHIKO.
SHE ISN'T REAL.
- HEY, WHY ARE YOU STILL UP?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE IN BED?
- OH. NO. I'M ACTUALLY LEAVING.
- ISN'T IT KIND OF
LATE FOR THAT?
- I HAVE SOMEONE
COMING OVER TO GET ME.
- WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
COMING TO GET YOU?
- I, UM... I JUST...
FUNNY STORY, THE TRUTH IS I'VE
ALWAYS HAD A CRUSH ON RYUTA,
LIKE BEFORE THIS STARTED,
BUT I WASN'T BRAVE
ENOUGH TO EVEN TALK TO HIM,
AND THEN, YOU KNOW,
I FOUND OUT I WAS
MOVING TO AMERICA,
AND I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SOME
MEMORIES WITH HIM
BEFORE I LEFT BECAUSE I'M
A GIRL LIKE THAT,
AND YOU KNOW HOW WE ARE.
SO THAT'S WHY I'VE BEEN...
- AND YOU LOST ME.
- I'M SORRY, BUT
AS IT TURNS OUT,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO PAY YOU BACK.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT. MICHIKO,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE, REMEMBER?
- ( gasping )
- HONESTLY, THERE'S A
LOT ABOUT THAT NIGHT
THAT I HAVE NO MEMORY OF.
IT'S SO BIZARRE.
BUT IF YOU HADN'T
BEEN THERE WITH ME,
I DOUBT I WOULD'VE BEEN LUCKY
ENOUGH TO SURVIVE ON MY OWN.
LOOK. AT LEAST SAY GOODBYE
TO MY LITTLE SISTER.
- I DON'T THINK I CAN, IT'S JUST
TOO HARD TO SAY GOODBYE.
- OH, IS IT NOW?
- IT IS. SO PLEASE, TELL HER.
TELL HER THAT...
I'LL, I'LL SEE HER AGAIN.
IT'S OKAY NOW, GUYS.
YOU CAN COME ON OUT.
- AS YOU WISH.
- HERE. WE HAVE FOUND
THE ITEM YOU REQUESTED.
BACK OFF. UNLESS YOU WANT TO
TURN INTO AN OLD PERVY MONK.
- ( hissing )
- PERFECT. NOW THEN, WE'RE
MORE THAN READY FOR THAT
SPECIAL REWARD YOU
PROMISED TO GIVE US.
- ( both exclaiming )
- ICHIKO. ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HUH? WHAT'S WRONG?
- UM, WHAT ABOUT OUR REWARD?
- ANOTHER TIME, OKAY?
- MAN. I GOT NEEDS.
- ANOTHER TIME, LIKE WHEN?
- Momiji: POOR LITTLE ICHIKO.
SHE HAD THE POWER TO
GET WHAT SHE WANTED.
IT WAS RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER.
BUT IT WASN'T
UNTIL THIS MOMENT
THAT SHE REALIZED WHAT IT WAS
SHE REALLY WANTED.
AND IT'S TOO LATE FOR HER, NOW.
THIS EPISODE IS KIND OF
BUMMING ME OUT.
I KNOW. I CAN GO AHEAD AND TURN
THIS GOOD FOR NOTHING TURTLE
INTO SOUP TO TAKE
MY MIND OFF THE WHOLE THING.
- THIS ISN'T VERY GODLY
BEHAVIOR, IF YOU ASK ME.
- MOTHERF...
- YOU SEE,
DID YOU JUST HEAR THAT?
YET ANOTHER INNOCENT
PERSON SOMEWHERE
HAS PAINFULLY JAMMED THEIR
PINKY TOE INTO A DRESSER.
WHILE WE'RE SITTING
AROUND WASTING TIME
BECAUSE OF ICHIKO SAKURA,
MORE AND MORE PEOPLE ARE
RUNNING OUT OF GOOD FORTUNE.
- ♪ THERE SHE IS, SWEETLY
BATTING HER EYELASHES, ♪
♪ FLIRTING WITH MY MAN LIKE
SHE DOESN'T KNOW I'M THERE... ♪
- ARE YOU
EVEN LISTENING, MOMIJI?
- ♪ YOU'RE A LOSER ♪
- I HEAR YOU FINE. BUT IT ISN'T
LIKE I'M SLACKING OFF OVER HERE.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, I'M TRYING TO
GET READY FOR ANOTHER BATTLE
WITH HER BY SUMMONING
MORE OF MY COURAGE.
- OH. IS THAT SO?
- WHO'S UP NEXT, GUYS?
- Bobby: OH MAN, THIS IS MY JAM.
- DON'T MAKE ANY SUDDEN
MOVEMENTS. THE OGRE IS HOME.
- OKAY? ( exhales ) SHE'S SCARY.
- NORMALLY, YEAH.
BUT FOR ICHIKO SAKURA,
THAT THERE WAS PRETTY TAME.
- TRUE STORY. EVER SINCE SHE
WAS TURNED INTO A CHILD,
SHE'S BEEN THERE IN BODY.
BUT NOT IN MIND.
- YOU'RE RIGHT. IT'S
NOT JUST HER MIND,
IT'S HER WHOLE
SPIRIT THAT'S GONE.
- AND SHE'S LIKE THIS ALL
THE TIME. SHE'S SO DEJECTED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO ABOUT IT.
WHENEVER I THINK I'VE FOUND
MY CHAdNCE AND ATTACK,
HER HAPPINESS ENERGY IS
STILL AS HIGH AS NORMAL.
I HADN'T NOTICED THIS.
THE SLIPPERS I'M USED TO SEEING
HER IN HAVE BEEN SWITCHED WITH
IRON WEIGHT TRAINERS
FOR SOME REASON.
- THIS IS A VERY SERIOUS CASE.
ALL, RIGHT, IT'S HIGH
TIME TO ADMINISTER
A LITTLE SHOCK THERAPY TO
SNAP HER OUT OF IT.
READY, SET, TITTIES.
VEGETA!
- WELL, THAT DIDN'T SEEM
TO DO ANYTHING, DID IT?
- MONK. I WANT YOU TO KNOW I
ACKNOWLEDGE YOUR COURAGE.
ALL RIGHT. IF ANYONE IS GONNA
SAVE THAT GIRL, IT'S ME.
- Female Voice: WOW!
- THAT WAS
WISHFUL THINKING, MONK.
SEXUAL HARASSMENT ISN'T
ENOUGH TO BRING ICHIKO BACK
TO HER OLD SELF.
- TAKE THIS AND LOVE IT,
YOU FILTHY MUTT.
- THIS IS WHAT SHE REALLY NEEDS.
ICHIKO SAKURA PUTS
THE "S" in S AND M.
- UM...
HEY, HOW YOU
FEELIN' THERE, ICHIKO?
NO. THIS ISN'T ICHIKO.
SHE'S AN IMPOSTER!
- ( screaming )
- MOMO'O, NO!
MY WARRIORS ARE DROPPING
LIKE FLIES. NO MORE.
APPARENTLY, I'LL HAVE TO
DEAL WITH THIS MYSELF.
FIVE MINUTES LEFT. IF
YOU'RE ALREADY FINISHED
KEEP CHECKING YOUR TEST
TO MAKE SURE YOU HAVEN'T
MADE ANY MISTAKES.
ALL RIGHT,
PUT YOUR PENCILS DOWN.
- ( students chattering )
HEY!
WHY WON'T YOU REACT?
DAMN, I HAD YAMABUKI
COME ALL THE WAY HERE, TOO.
WELL, AT LEAST THE CLASS
HASN'T NOTICED ANYTHING IS UP.
I BET THEY JUST FIGURE
I'M DOING SOMETHING WEIRD AGAIN,
BECAUSE THAT'S USUALLY
WHAT I'M DOING.
- THAT MOMIJI'S DOING
SOMETHING WEIRD AGAIN.
- ( sighs and gasps )
- IT'S SO HARD TO
SLEEP THROUGH A TEST.
- HEY, UH... SO...
UM... TSUWA...
( sighs )
- ( exclaims )
I SEE, SO THAT MUST BE WHAT
THIS WHOLE THING'S ABOUT.
OH MY, DID SPRINGTIME
JUST COME FOR ICHIKO?
YOU LITTLE DEVIL, YOU.
YOU DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
WHY, IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE WE'RE BLOWING UP
BIRDS WITH RICE.
GO ON, GIRL, GET HIM.
GET YOUR MAN.
- ( sighs )
- WHAT? UGH!
I WAS TALKING TO YOU.
SHOCK POSITIVELY IGNORED.
( screaming angrily )
ICHIKO, YOU IDIOT!
- WELL, LET'S HAVE IT. I'M READY
TO HEAR YOUR REGULAR REPORT.
I HOPE YOU'VE GOT GOOD NEWS.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU?
- HOW DO YOU EXPECT ME
TO WORK LIKE THIS?
YOU'RE BEING DRAMATIC.
- ALL RIGHT, MOMIJI. LET ME BE
PERFECTLY CLEAR.
IT MAY SURPRISE YOU, BUT
EVEN I HAVE LIMITS.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP ON
FOREVER LIKE THIS,
I CAN EASILY HAVE ANOTHER
POVERTY GOD SWITCH WITH YOU.
- YEAH. THAT MAY NOT BE
A BAD IDEA.
WHEN I THINK OF ALL THE CRAP
I'VE HAD TO PUT UP WITH
FROM THAT MORON.
IT ISN'T JUST THAT I THINK
THIS IS ANNOYING.
IT'S THAT IT'S ALL SO
UTTERLY FRUITLESS.
- ( sighs )
- ( grunts )
WHY? I HATE IT! WHAT
THE HELL IS GOING ON WITH ME?
WHY SHOULD I HAVE
TO BE SO MIXED-UP
OVER SOMETHING SO STUPID?
IT'S JUST A HANDKERCHIEF.
I FORGOT I HAD IT, AND NOW
I CAN'T GET RID OF IT.
WHY CAN'T I JUST GO AHEAD AND
GIVE THE DAMN THING BACK.
IT'S SO FREAKIN' SIMPLE,
AND I CAN'T DO IT.
HERE, YOU MUST HAVE
DROPPED THIS OR SOMETHING.
- OH...
THANK YOU.
- WHY IS YOUR
ADDRESS WRITTEN ON IT?
LIKE, WHAT, ARE YOU STILL
IN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL?
BECAUSE OF EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED
I CAN'T EVEN LOOK TSUWABUKI
IN THE FACE ANYMORE!
SO WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO ABOUT THAT?
OH, I KNOW. I CAN JUST
DROP IT OFF AT HIS HOUSE
AND NOT SAY ANYTHING.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- UH, I, UH...
( imitating chicken clucking )
- WHAT ARE YOU A CHICKEN?
HEY HOLD ON, THIS IS MINE.
YOU CAME HERE JUST TO
GIVE THIS TO ME?
- UM - HMM. UM - HMM. UM - HMM.
- ( thinking ) WHAT'S
WRONG WITH HER?
I WONDER IF MICHIKO
DROPPED IT WHEN SHE LEFT.
- WHY ARE YOU REMEMBERING THAT?
- GUESS YOU'RE
GETTING IN THE HABIT
OF BRINGING STUFF BACK TO ME.
THANKS A LOT. AND I'M SORRY IF
IT WAS ANY TROUBLE.
- YOU'RE APOLOGIZING TO ME?
YEAH. YEAH. THAT'S GOOD.
- HUH?
- WELL, YOU SHOULD
BE GRATEFUL. SEE YA.
- WAIT, WHAT?
SOMETHING'S SERIOUSLY
WRONG WITH HER.
- I REALLY DID IT.
I GAVE IT BACK. I GAVE IT
BACK! I GAVE IT BACK!
THE WEIGHT HAS
FINALLY BEEN LIFTED.
I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER.
THIS IS TOTALLY AWESOME.
IT FEELS REFRESHING,
LIKE RIGHT AFTER PUTTING ON A
NEW PAIR OF UNDERWEAR
ON NEW YEAR'S DAY MORNING.
THE FOG THAT WAS BLOCKING MY
VIEW HAS FINALLY CLEARED AND...
WHAT?
WHAT IN THE HELL
HAVE YOU DONE?
I SEE YOU GUYS
HELPED YOURSELVES.
WHAT KIND OF A JERK GOD,
TAKES ADVANTAGE OF HOSPITALITY?
- THAT PRESENCE. YES. IT'S HER.
THE OLD ICHIKO IS BACK!
OH, YEAH. THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
- REPLACE ME? HOW DARE YOU.
- WAIT. WHAT ABOUT BEFORE?
- I TOLD YOU I WAS GONNA BE
THE ONE TO TAKE HER DOWN.
DON'T GET ALL SENILE.
- GIRL, WHAT IS
YOUR DAMN PROBLEM?
DUE TO TIME CONSTRAINTS,
VIEWERS HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY
TO FIND THIS WEEK'S NADESHIKO
ON THEIR OWN.
- WAIT, NO, THIS CAN'T
BE HAPPENING... NO...
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING... NO,
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING, NO...