- SO, DO YOU HAVE THE PACKAGE?
- THERE'S NO NEED TO BE
IN SUCH A RUSH.
I'VE GOT IT WITH ME,
JUST LIKE I SAID I WOULD.
- YES, INDEED YOU DO.
AND NOW IT IS MINE.
IT CERTAINLY PAYS TO HAVE
OLD FRIENDS, DOESN'T IT?
THIS IS THE LEAST I CAN DO
IN RETURN.
- UH! NO, THANK YOU.
- OH, YOU!
- I SERIOUSLY DON'T WANT IT.
WELL, OUR BUSINESS HERE IS DONE.
I'LL GUESS
I'LL BE ON MY WAY THEN.
- UH, WHAT IS THAT?
- I THINK IT'S A TURTLE.
- ( laughing )
- Urashimako: EXCUSE ME, GUYS,
I'M GONNA NEED TO GET
THROUGH THAT DOOR.
- OH, GREAT.
WHAT IS SHE UP TO NOW?
- HUH?
MAYBE IT'S SOMETHING
FROM SUWANO.
THIS DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE HIS HANDWRITING.
WHY'S SHE GETTING
PACKAGES DELIVERED HERE
INSTEAD OF HELL OR
WHEREVER SHE'S FROM?
I BET SHE DECIDED TO HAVE
ONE OF THOSE STUPID LITTLE
POVERTY GOD ITEMS SENT
TO HER HERE.
THEN YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
GO AHEAD AND TAKE CARE OF IT
BEFORE IT CAN EVER GET TO HER,
SHOULDN'T YOU?
( laughing )
IT'S NOT GONNA SUDDENLY EXPLODE
OR ANYTHING, RIGHT?
MEH! SEEMS SAFE ENOUGH.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HOW MAD
SHE IS AT ME FOR THIS!
( coughing )
WHAT THE HELL?
- YOU FELL FOR IT, YOU FOOL!
YOU JUST OPENED A TREASURE BOX
GIVEN TO ME BY URASHIMAKO
MIZUNOE, THE URASHIMA-TARO GOD!
URASHIMA-TARO GODS
ARE THE DEITIES
OF LONG LIFE AND MARRIAGE,
WHICH CONNECT THIS EXISTENCE
WITH THE WORLD OF IMMORTALITY.
I'LL HAVE NO PROBLEM TAKING
YOUR HAPPINESS ENERGY
AWAY FROM YOU NOW THAT
YOU'RE AN OLD WOMAN!
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO HAVE THOSE
BREASTS YOU'RE SO PROUD OF
TURN INTO UGLY AND SAGGY SACKS?
( laughing evilly )
WAIT.
- HUH? I'M... I'M SMALL.
UH...
- IDIOT TURTLE!
HE MUST'VE GOTTEN HIS TREASURE
BOXES MIXED UP.
THIS WILL BE FINE, THOUGH.
- SO! I MAY BE SMALLER,
BUT MY SOMIN SHORAI
COULD STILL KICK YOUR ASS!
OH, NO! MY SOMIN SHORAI GOT
TURNED ALL ITTY BITTY SIZED TOO.
- HUH.
- YEAH, WELL, STILL. COME FORTH,
MY TWELVE DIVINE GENERALS!
NO, THEY'VE ALL BEEN TURNED INTO
BABY VERSIONS OF THEMSELVES,
AND I HATE IT!
( crying )
- IT WOULDN'T BE FUN FOR ME
IF I TOOK YOUR HAPPINESS ENERGY
AWAY TOO FAST.
SO FIRST, I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
BACK ALL THE HUMILIATION
I'VE HAD TO ENDURE
THANKS TO YOU.
TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHAT'S IT LIKE TO BE
FRESH OUT OF BOOBIES, HUH?
WHICH ONE OF US IS
FLAT-CHESTED AGAIN?
( laughing )
- YEAH, NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE ABOUT
THE SAME CUP SIZE.
- ( screams)
CUP SIZE THIS, BITCH!
( gasps )
- ( groaning )
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
THAT MUST BE SOME KIND OF
MISTAKE! A MALFUNCTION!
DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT!
- ( screaming )
- NO! IT'S MEAN AND HATEFUL AND
SO UNFAIR AND KEEP AN EYE ON HER
BECAUSE I'M GONNA GO BUY
MY FAVORITE TORTURE ITEM!
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MONEY?
REALLY? IT'S NOT THAT EXPENSIVE.
BUMMER! GUESS I'LL JUST
GO FIND SOMETHING
AROUND THE HOUSE TO USE THEN.
( gasps )
HEY! GET BACK HERE! STOP!
- ( grunts with effort )
- HAVE YOU LOST YOUR TINY MIND?
WHAT? NO WAY! HA!
QUIT GOING SO FAST.
- ( children laughing )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
LOOK AT ME! I'M RIDICULOUS.
SHE'S PROBABLY STILL
PROWLING AROUND UP THERE.
I BETTER STAY HERE.
IF SHE FINDS ME, I'M HISTORY.
- HA! I FOUND YOU!
- MIKA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I DON'T KNOW. IS THIS GIRL
ONE OF YOUR FRIENDS?
- THAT GIRL?
NO, I DON'T KNOW HER.
- Ichiko: I'VE MET HER BEFORE.
THAT GIRL CALLED
HER MIKA, RIGHT?
MIKA...
( gasps )
OF COURSE!
I REMEMBER NOW!
SHE'S TSUWABUKI'S SISTER!
- HEY! WE'RE PLAYING HIDE AND
SEEK. DO YOU WANNA PLAY WITH US?
COME ON!
WE'RE HAVING LOTS OF FUN!
- THANK YOU, NO. I SHOULDN'T.
I DON'T KNOW WHY, THOUGH.
YEAH, SURE, OKAY.
ON SECOND THOUGHT, I WOULD
REALLY LIKE TO PLAY WITH YOU.
- I KNEW YOU WOULD. IT'S OKAY
IF SHE JOINS US, RIGHT?
- Both: THAT'S TOTALLY OKAY.
- HEY, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
I'M MIKA TSUWABUKI.
IT'S SO VERY NICE TO MEET YOU!
- OH, MY NAME?
IT'S UM-UH... MI... MICHIKO.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU, TOO.
- HEY, ICHIKO.
WHERE ARE YOU?
I BLAME YOU.
IF YOU HADN'T BROKEN THE SCOUTER
WE'D HAVE FOUND HER.
GOOD JOB. I HOPE
YOU'RE PROUD OF YOURSELF.
BUT I'LL DEAL WITH YOU
WHEN WE GET HOME.
WE STILL HAVE A LITTLE BRAT
TO TRACK DOWN.
- ( girls gigglng )
- OH, THOSE ARE JUST
REGULAR KIDS.
- ( breathing heavily )
- Non-Chan: BYE BYE! I HAD FUN!
- Kana: SEE YOU TOMORROW!
- SEE YOU GUYS LATER!
HEY, MICHIKO,
DON'T YOU HAVE TO GO HOME, TOO?
- CRAPPERS! UP TO NOW, I COULD
BLEND IN WITH THOSE KIDS EASY,
BUT BEING OUT
THIS LATE BY MYSELF
WILL MAKE ME STICK OUT
LIKE A SORE THUMB.
WAIT! I'VE GOT IT!
UM, WOULD IT BE OKAY IF I WENT
TO YOUR HOUSE TO PLAY SOME MORE,
MAYBE? PRETTY PLEASE?
- WAIT, YOU WANNA GO
TO MY HOUSE?
- CAN I? YOU DON'T MIND, DO YOU?
- SAY YES, PLEASE! IT'S NOT LIKE
MY PLACE IS SAFE FOR ME,
AND I DON'T HAVE
ANYWHERE ELSE I CAN GO
WHERE I'LL BE ABLE
TO STAY HIDDEN
FROM THAT DANG POVERTY GOD.
MOST OF ALL, THERE'S NO
WAY IN WAY IN HELL
THIS GIRL IS GOING TO
SLEEP OUTSIDE!
- SURE! LET'S GO THEN.
- DO YOU MEAN IT?
- OF COURSE.
IT'S RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER.
( humming )
- ( sighs with relief )
WELL, AT LEAST I DON'T HAVE TO
SLEEP OUTSIDE.
NOW IF I CAN JUST FIND A WAY
TO GET MY NORMAL BODY BACK.
I DON'T HAVE A CLUE HOW
I'M GONNA MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
- I REALLY LIKE
YOUR DRESS, MICHIKO.
- THERE'S NO ONE AROUND
WHO'LL UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON, EITHER.
- Bobby: ONLY QUESTION ASKING!
- Akane: LET GO OF ME!
- JUST WANT KNOWING WHERE
AT KINKAKUJI TEMPLE IS.
- YOU WON'T STOP LEERING AT ME,
SO OBVIOUSLY YOU HAVE
AN ULTERIOR MOTIVE!
- WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
- MIKA, I'M SORRY. I LEFT
SOMETHING BACK AT THE PARK.
YOU GO ON AHEAD
AND I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU
IN A LITTLE BIT.
- OKAY!
HOW? YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
TO MY HOUSE BEFORE.
- OH, I'LL BE RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- OKAY, I'LL WALK SLOWLY, THEN!
- Bobby: GIVE IT UP TO ME!
DON'T FIGHT IT!
- GROSS! WHAT KIND OF MONK
TRIES TO MOLEST PEOPLE?
- THAT'S GOOD. NICE KICK.
LIFT YOUR LEG HIGHER.
- YOU'RE ACTUALLY USING A PUPPY
TO SHIELD YOURSELF FROM ME?
POOR BABY. IT'S A PERSON!
IT TURNED INTO A MAN!
- WOW, YOUR KICK
IS AMAZING, BABE.
SO, DO YOU HAVE SOME SORT OF
SPECIAL COMBAT TRAINING OR WHAT?
- THIS IS BAD. THESE GUYS THINK
THEY'RE IN A HENTAI.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE. RUN!
- PLEASE LET ME HELP YOU
TRAIN! I WOULD BE HAPPY
IF YOU THOUGHT OF ME AS
YOUR PUNCHING BAG!
MAKE ME HAPPY!
AND WE GOT RUN OFF ON AGAIN.
- Young Ichiko:
HEY, BOBBY! MOMO'O!
- Both: HUH?
- WHO THE HECK IS THIS?
SOME KIND OF MINIATURE
FRIEND OF YOURS?
- YEAH, NO.
- DON'T YOU RECOGNIZE ME?
ICHIKO SAKURA!
- ( both gasp )
- ARE ALL LITTLE GIRLS
SPECIAL IN THE HEAD,
OR IS THAT ONE EXTRA SPECIAL?
- FOR THE RECORD,
LOLI ISN'T EVEN MY TYPE.
- RIGHT. I DON'T SEE HOW
RIDICULOUS AMOUNTS OF RUFFLES
ARE SUPPOSED TO GET A MAN
IN THE MOOD, MAN.
- IF YOU LOSERS CAN'T IMAGINE
WHO I AM IN YOUR HEADS,
THEN MAYBE YOUR BODIES
WILL PAY ATTENTION!
- THIS NECK HOLD IS DEFINITELY
A CLASSIC ICHIKO SAKURA.
- MOMO'O, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE A DOG,
ISN'T YOUR NOSE TELLING YOU
WHO I REALLY AM?
- IT IS. AND I KNEW THE TRUTH
ALL ALONG. IN FACT, TO BE HONEST
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
BECAUSE I WAS HOPING
THINGS WOULD END UP LIKE THIS.
- Bobby: I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
SO HAPPY, DAWG!
- OH, YEAH,
THERE'S TOTALLY A WAY
TO TURN YOU BACK TO YOURSELF.
- REALLY?
- A TREASURE BOX MADE YOU YOUNG
BUT THERE'S ANOTHER TYPE
OF TREASURE BOX,
ONE THAT MAKES YOU OLDER.
- IF I HAD THAT, THEN I COULD
GO BACK TO NORMAL?
- PROBABLY.
- THEN I HAVE A HUGE FAVOR
TO ASK THE TWO OF YOU.
COULD YOU PLEASE FIND THAT
OTHER BOX FOR ME?
IF I GO LOOKING FOR IT OUT
IN THE OPEN LIKE THIS,
SHE'LL FIND ME FOR SURE.
I PROMISE, IF YOU FIND
THAT BOX FOR ME,
I'LL GIVE YOU WHATEVER
YOU WANT. PLEASE?
- Both: DO YOU MEAN IT?
- I'LL GIVE YOU WHATEVER YOU
WANT, ALL RIGHT.
UH...
- Both: LET'S FIND THAT BOX!
ATTACK WITH A UNITED FRONT AND
ALL OUR DREAMS WILL COME TRUE!
- NO! I MEANT MONEY
AND FOOD AND STUFF.
WHATEVER YOU THINK I MEANT
BY WHATEVER YOU WANT IS WRONG!
- WE ARE ON IT, NOW.
TAKE THIS! IF ANYTHING HAPPENS,
FEEL FREE TO CALL ME.
- WHAT IS THIS?
A WHISTLE? WEIRD.
- PREPARE YOURSELF.
THE CHALLENGE AHEAD SHALL
NOT BE AN EASY ONE.
- LET MY NOSE LEAD
US INTO BATTLE!
- YEAH!
- MAYBE IT WASN'T TOO SMART
TO ASK FOR THEIR HELP.
IT'S NOT LIKE
THERE'S ANYONE ELSE, THOUGH.
- WE'RE HERE! IT MIGHT BE
A LITTLE CRAMPED. I'M HOME!
- THIS IS THE SECOND TIME
I'VE BEEN HERE.
IT'S BETTER THAN SLEEPING
OUTSIDE, BUT BARELY.
( sighs )
- OH, YOU BROUGHT A FRIEND
HOME WITH YOU.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU,
I'M RIKA.
- WE'RE THE ONLY GIRLS
IN THE FAMILY.
MY BROTHER'S OVER THERE.
HIS NAME'S RYUTA.
- I KNOW.
- THIS IS MY BABY
BROTHER, SORATA.
HEY, CAN YOU SAY
HI TO MY NEW FRIEND?
- HI. HOW ARE YOU
DOIN' THERE, SLUGGER?
HOLY MOTHER CRAP!
HE'S SUSPICIOUS.
HE KNOWS SOMETHING'S UP.
- ( laughing nervously )
CLOSE CALL DOT COM.
- Tsuwabuki: I'M HOME.
- AND THERE'S THE BIG BOSS.
- THAT'S MY OLDEST BROTHER.
LET'S SEE, WHAT'S
HIS NAME AGAIN?
IT'S, UH... KEITA, I THINK.
( giggles )
- TSUWABUKI. FOUND A NEW FRIEND?
- YEP. HER NAME IS MICHIKO.
- OH, HELLO. HOW ARE YOU?
- HMM.
- I'M GOOD. HAVE WE MET
SOMEWHERE BEFORE?
MY MISTAKE, I GUESS.
- ( sighs with relief )
I'M NOT DONE YET.
THIS IS ABOUT TO GET REAL.
- Tsuwabuki: YOU WANNA STAY
OVER HERE?
- YES, PLEASE.
SHOULDN'T WE CALL YOUR PARENTS
FIRST AND ASK THEM?
- UM, WE CAN'T DO THAT.
- AND WHY IS THAT?
- BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE A MOTHER
OR A FATHER TO CALL ANYMORE.
I HAVE NO OTHER
RELATIVES, OR FAMILY,
OR EVEN A HOME TO LIVE IN.
- WELL, YOU SHOULD BE
WITH THE POLICE, NOT US.
- I FORGOT! THAT WAS ALL A LIE!
THE TRUTH IS I'M JUST REALLY
AFRAID OF MY FATHER.
HE GETS DRUNK AND BEATS MY
MOTHER AND ME ALMOST EVERY DAY.
I RAN AWAY FROM HOME
BECAUSE OF IT.
- I'M GONNA SHOW THAT GUY
A REAL BEATING.
- NO, I WAS LYING
ABOUT THAT, TOO!
I JUST WANNA STAY HERE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
DO I HAVE TO HAVE A GOOD REASON
TO BE HERE?
- SOUNDS LIKE A LONG STORY
TO ME.
NO, STAY IF YOU WANT TO.
THE BATHROOM STINKS THOUGH.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH!
I'LL MAKE SURE TO
PAY YOU BACK SOMEHOW!
- PAY US BACK?
( gasps )
OH, HOLY CRAP!
COULD THIS BE
SOME RICH FAMILY'S DAUGHTER?
- THANK YOU, SON, HERE'S
A TOKEN OF OUR GRATITUDE.
- YOU CALL THIS A TOKEN?
WOW! WITH THIS MUCH,
I COULD BUY US ALL A HOUSE,
SOCCER BALLS, AND NEW CLOTHES!
- All: YOU'RE THE BEST
BIG BROTHER, EVER!
- JUST A LITTLE WHILE LONGER,
YOU GUYS, I PROMISE.
JUST HANG IN THERE
WITH ME A LITTLE LONGER!
- WHY ARE YOU CRYING, DUDE?
IT'S WEIRD.
- All: THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
- Ryuta: MIKA, YOUR FRIED PRAWN
IS BIGGER THAN MINE,
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
- NO, IT ISN'T.
- Rika: HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU
NOT TO POINT YOUR CHOPSTICKS
AT OTHERS?
WE'RE NOT BARBARIANS!
I'M SORRY WE'RE SUCH
A LOUD FAMILY, MICHIKO.
- IT'S SURPRISING HOW CONSISTENT
THINGS IN THIS HOUSE CAN BE.
- IT'S TRUE. ISN'T THIS LIKE
THE SECOND TIME WE'VE FOUGHT
WHILE WE HAD A GUEST OVER?
- Ryuta: YEAH, WE FOUGHT
WITH TIT-CHIKO, TOO.
- HOW CAN HE STILL BE
USING THAT NAME?
- Rika: THAT GIRL.
WHAT WAS HER PROBLEM?
OH! SHE WAS SO RUDE.
JUST SO RUDE.
SHE CAME INTO OUR HOME
AND STARTED MAKING FUN OF US.
AND FOR WHAT?
FOR NOT WANTING HER MONEY?
FOR NOT BEING RICH LIKE HER?
- TALK ABOUT HOLDING A GRUDGE.
- UH-OH. RIKA'S GONE INTO
BIG BAD SISTER MODE.
- I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
BE STRESSING ABOUT THAT GIRL.
- YOU'RE GONNA GIVE YOURSELF
WRINKLES, YA KNOW.
- I'M ONLY IN MIDDLE SCHOOL!
I DON'T HAVE WRINKLES!
OKAY, FINE. I WON'T TALK
ABOUT HER AGAIN.
- WELL, I'VE GOTTA GET TO WORK.
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
- IT'S ALREADY THAT LATE?
- LUCKILY, I GOT TOMORROW OFF,
SO WE CAN ALL HANG OUT TOGETHER.
- FOR REAL?
- YAY!
- ALL RIGHT, I'M OFF.
- All: HAVE FUN!
SEE YOU TOMORROW!
- WHAT'S SUPPOSED TO
HAPPEN TOMORROW?
- WE'RE GOING ON A PICNIC!
- WOULD YOU LIKE TO
COME WITH US, MICHIKO?
- UM...
- YEAH, COME WITH US.
IT'LL BE FUN!
- OH. SURE.
- BEST PICNIC EVER!
I'M SO EXCITED, I CAN'T WAIT!
- WHAT IS THIS? I FELT IT
LAST TIME I WAS OVER, TOO.
IT'S NOT LIKE
I'LL BE HERE FOREVER.
SO WHY IS THIS HOUSE SO
STIFLING? I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I JUST FEEL SO ANXIOUS
AND AWKWARD HERE.
- YES. I CAN SENSE
THE BOX IS THIS WAY.
- I THINK YOU'RE WRONG.
- PERHAPS WE SHOULD GO INTO
ONE OF THESE FINE ESTABLISHMENTS
TO LOOK FOR CLUES.
- GOOD IDEA. GOOD PLAN.
LET'S DO IT!
- I'M NOT SURE WHY, BUT
I'M STARTING TO GET EXCITED.
- I THINK I KNOW WHY.
- Momiji: THIS IS YOUR FAULT!
IF YOU'D TAKEN YOUR HEAD
OUT OF YOUR SHELL
AND PAID ATTENTION TO WHAT
TREASURE BOX WAS WHAT,
NONE OF THIS WOULD'VE HAPPENED!
- NO WAY, YOU CAN'T BLAME ME.
AND BESIDES, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO LET A LITTLE GIRL
GET AWAY FROM YOU!
- I SAID IT'S YOUR FAULT!
- AGREE TO DISAGREE. WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO DO ABOUT IT?
- JUST GET YOUR TREASURE
BOXES READY ASAP.
ONE TO TURN HER BACK TO NORMAL,
AND ANOTHER ONE THAT
WILL MAKE HER AN OLD WOMAN.
- I CAN'T DO THAT!
AFTER ALL I WENT THROUGH TO GET
THAT FIRST ONE OUT OF HERE.
NOW YOU EXPECT ME TO
GET YOU TWO MORE?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW PISSED
OFF THE PRINCESS WOULD BE
IF SHE KNEW WHAT I WAS DOING?
- UNDERSTOOD. NEVER MIND.
- ( sighs with relief )
- INSTEAD, START
SAYING YOUR PRAYERS,
BECAUSE THE NEXT TIME
I SEE YOU,
THE PRINCESS WILL BE
THE LEAST OF YOUR WORRIES.
I'LL BET YOU CAN GET PLENTY OF
SOUP STOCK FROM A LIVE TURTLE
THAT HAS LIVED
FOR OVER 1,000 YEARS.
- NO, YOU CAN'T DO THAT TO ME!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT!
I'LL MANAGE SOMETHING! BUT
I'M GONNA NEED A WEEK AT LEAST.
- YOU GOT THREE DAYS. ANY MORE
THAN THAT AND YOU'RE SOUP.
- ( wails )
- YOU KNOW, EVEN IF I CAN
GET THE TREASURE BOXES,
UNLESS I FIND HER,
WHAT'S THE POINT?
GEEZ. WHERE DID YOU GO,
ICHIKO? COME BACK TO ME!
OH, YEAH. OF COURSE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE PLACE SHE
COULD HAVE GONE,
WHY DIDN'T I THINK OF IT BEFORE?
- ( loud screaming )
- YEP. IT SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD DAY
FOR A PICNIC.
HUH? THAT'S NO FUN.
WHO WET THE BED?
- OH, IT WAS MICHIKO.
- SUCKS FOR HER.
HUH?
- I AM SO SORRY.
( voice-over ) WHEN I WAS TURNED
BACK INTO A CHILD,
MY STUPID BLADDER
GOT TURNED BACK, TOO.
- YOU HAVE NOTHING TO
APOLOGIZE FOR, MICHIKO.
IT HAPPENS.
WE CAN WASH THE BEDDING.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL AT ALL.
- I'M 16 YEARS OLD AND
I JUST PEED IN SOMEONE'S BED.
I WISH I COULD CRAWL
INTO A HOLE AND DIE.
- OH, IT'S OKAY, HONEY.
- DON'T CRY. PLEASE. OH, NO.
- I'VE NEVER BEEN SO HUMILIATED.
THIS IS ALL HER FAULT.
ONCE I GET BACK TO
MY NORMAL SELF,
I'M GONNA KILL
THAT DAMN POVERTY GOD.
- I FOUND YOU.
- Mika: ♪ LA, LA, LA, LA ♪
♪ TODAY WE'RE GOING ON THE
BEST PICNIC EVER IN THE WORLD ♪
- HOW NICE! A PICNIC.
- YES, MA'AM,
WE'RE ALL VERY EXCITED ABOUT IT.
- YOU THINK WE'LL SEE
RHINOCEROS BEETLES?
- DOUBTFUL. IT'S STILL
JUST A LITTLE TOO EARLY.
- ( laughing )
- ♪ LA, LA, LA, LA ♪
♪ TODAY WE'RE GOING ON THE
BEST PICNIC EVER IN THE WORLD ♪
( chuckles )
- Mika: WE'RE HERE!
- ( laughs )
HERE IT COMES!
- EVERYONE'S SO ENERGETIC.
ALL THIS TIME, I THOUGHT
I WAS IN PRETTY GOOD SHAPE.
- Ryuta: MICHIKO! HEADS UP!
- HUH? AAAAHH!
- OH, NO! MICHIKO!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
- Tsuwabuki: ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT, MICHIKO? -
GEEZ, WHAT THE CRAP WAS THAT?
- HERE YOU CAN
USE MY HANDKERCHIEF
TO WIPE OFF WHERE YOU GOT DIRTY.
- A HANKIE?
THAT'S A SURPRISE.
NO WAY! IS THIS IN CASE HE
LOSES IT? WHAT A CHEAPO!
- IF MIKA HAD TAKEN
THAT KIND OF TUMBLE,
SHE'D BE CRYING HER EYES OUT
RIGHT NOW.
BUT NOT YOU,
YOU DIDN'T CRY AT ALL.
THAT'S A GOOD GIRL, MICHIKO.
- STOP! DON'T TREAT ME
LIKE I'M A CHILD!
- Rika: AAAAAH! KEITA!
- WOW, DO YOU THINK
I MIGHT HAVE MADE HER ANGRY?
- YES! WHAT ON EARTH DID YOU SAY
TO THAT POOR GIRL?
- ( panting )
CRAP! I HATE THIS!
WHAT'S GOING ON? IT'S SO WEIRD.
I CAN'T EVEN LOOK AT TSUWABUKI
WITHOUT GETTING ALL FREAKED OUT.
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE
HE'S TREATING ME LIKE A KID.
UGH, I DON'T LIKE THIS.
- ( squeaking )
- HUH?
- GET OUT! THEY'RE EVERYWHERE!
WAIT! WHY IS THAT ONE SO MUCH
BIGGER THAN THE OTHERS?
( screams )
KUMAGAI? WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- OH, YEAH!
GOT A BIG ONE HERE!
WELL, CRIKEY MATE!
THE MOMIJI SQUAD
HAS DISCOVERED A NEW, YET,
UGLY SPECIES!
- OH, NO! DAMN POVERTY GOD.
- PRINCESS, YOU READY?
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN WAITING
A LONG TIME FOR THIS.
OH, NO! YOU'RE SEPARATED FROM
TSUWABUKI AND HIS FAMILY.
AND I BROUGHT ALONG
MY SOMIN SHORAI
JUST TO BE SAFE, TOO.
BUT I LEFT IT
AND MOMO'O'S WHISTLE IN MY
BACKPACK, SO, SO MUCH FOR THAT!
- MICHIKO, WHERE ARE YOU?
WE'RE LEAVING! HEY, MICHIKO!
- MICHIKO, LET'S GO!
- OH, WHAT DO WE DO?
WHAT IF SHE'S GOTTEN LOST
OR HURT OR SOMETHING WORSE?
- YEAH, WAY TO GO, KEITA.
YOU MADE HER MAD
AND NOW SHE'S
TOTALLY GONNA DIE.
- YOU ARE NOT HELPING, RYU.
- YOU GO ON AHEAD
DOWN THE MOUNTAIN.
TAKE CARE OF
EVERYONE ELSE FOR NOW,
AND HOPEFULLY
I CAN FIND HER.
WE DON'T HAVE
A WHOLE LOT OF LIGHT LEFT.
YOU GUYS CAN WAIT FOR ME
AT THE BUS STOP, OKAY?
YOU KNOW, THE ONE
BY THE HEAD OF THE TRAIL.
HEY, WITH ANY LUCK,
MICHIKO MIGHT ALREADY BE THERE.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME,
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE BACK BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT.
- UH. YEAH.
KEITA, BE CAREFUL, OKAY?
- WILL DO. ALWAYS AM!
MICHIKO! HEY, MICHIKO!
I'M STARTING TO THINK
WE SHOULD GET A SEARCH PARTY.
HER SHOE!
WHY IS THERE JUST ONE?
PLEASE LET HER BE OKAY.
THAT'S NOT A GOOD SIGN. TELL ME
SHE DIDN'T FALL DOWN THERE.
OH, NO.
( screams )
- Bobby: I SENSE TODAY WE WILL
FIND A LEAD IN THIS STORE.
- Momo'o: WRONG! IT'S THAT ONE!
- WAIT, WHAT ARE WE
LOOKING FOR AGAIN?
- UH, BOOBS?
- ( chuckles )
- Students: THIS WEEK'S...
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO!
SORRY TO KEEP YOU
WAITING, EVERYONE!
IN THIS SEGMENT EACH WEEK,
MY MAGNIFICENT EXPLOITS
CALL INTO DOUBT THE UNMETHODICAL
AND DISRESPECTFUL NATURES
OF THE ANIMATION STAFF,
AS WE TAKE A LOOK BACK,
WILLY-NILLY, WITH TIME LEFT
OVER FROM THE MAIN EPISODE.
THIS WEEK I WAS HERE, AND AS AN
ADDED BONUS, I WAS OVER HERE!
NOW THAT WE'VE BEEN
ON THE AIR FOR OVER A MONTH,
FINALLY THOSE ON THE ANIMATION
STAFF WHO HAD THEIR DOUBTS,
WONDERING, "HUH? THIS SEGMENT
MAKES NO SENSE
"TO THOSE WHO HAVEN'T READ
THE ORIGINAL MANGA, DOES IT?",
CAN ALL GO TO HELL! YOU DON'T
KNOW ME, SO BACK OFF MY MOMENT!
I'M TRYING TO SHINE!