- AW, SUWANO SENT A LETTER
FROM HIS HONEYMOON.
- MY DEAR MISS ICHIKO,
HOW IS LIFE ON YOUR OWN?
WE ARE HAVING A GRAND TIME
AND WISH YOU WERE HERE.
PLEASE TAKE CARE AND
GIVE MY REGARDS
TO YOUR NURSE FRIEND, AS WELL.
- SO ANNOYING. I TOLD HIM,
SHE'S NOT MY FRIEND.
- ( laughing ) COLOR ME
THOROUGHLY AMUSED.
THIS SHOW IS FREAKING HILARE.
- Man: DON'T E-MAIL ME
YOUR CAT MEMES
'CAUSE I AIN'T GONNA READ THEM.
- OH, HELL NO. YOU DO NOT GET
TO LOUNGE AROUND
WATCHING TRASHY TALK
SHOWS ALL DAY.
- ( laughing )
- CUT IT OUT.
- CALM DOWN. YOU KNOW,
YOU SHOULD BE THANKING ME
FOR STAYING HERE.
IT'S GONNA MAKE THINGS
A LOT EASIER ON YOU.
AS LONG AS I'M HERE,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT SUCKING THE HAPPINESS
ENERGY OUT OF ANYONE.
LOOK AT IT LIKE AN AUTOMATIC
WITHDRAWAL OR CONVENIENCE FEE.
ALL MADE POSSIBLE BY THIS GUY.
INTRODUCING THE
POVERTY GOD ITEM,
MISTER ENERGY BARRIER EMITTER.
HE'S MORE THAN JUST
ADORABLE, KIDS!
WHEN USED BY SOMEONE
WITH INTENSE HAPPINESS ENERGY,
HE AUTOMATICALLY REPELS
INCOMING DOOM, GLOOM,
AND, YES, UNHAPPINESS.
AND WHEN USED BY ANOTHER
WITH STRONG UNHAPPINESS ENERGY,
THE HAPPINESS THAT HAS
BEEN SIPHONED
BOUNCES BACK TO THE
ORIGINAL OWNER.
AND WE BOTH AGREE,
YOU CAN'T AFFORD
TO MAKE ANYONE ELSE UNHAPPY.
- ( groans ) MOMMA.
- THAT BACON BIT THE DUST HARD.
YOU REALIZE THERE'S NO ONE
I KNOW WORTH ACTUALLY LIKING
BESIDES SUWANO, RIGHT?
WHY SHOULD I CARE IF RANDOM
JACK OR JILL ARE HAPPY?
LOOK, JUST GO BACK
TO FLATTY FLAT ISLAND.
I'LL HAVE THEM BAKE
A SHEET CAKE IN YOUR HONOR.
- NO, YOU DIDN'T. HOW DARE
YOU SAY THAT TO ME.
IT'S CALLED THE LAND
OF THE POVERTY GODS
AND YOU'RE ASKING FOR A
ONE-WAY-TICKET, JUMBO JUGS.
SEND ME AND ALL
THE OTHER HOT GIRLS
YOU'RE THREATENED BY THERE.
WHEN ALL THE SEXY CHICK
MAGAZINES ARE OUTTA PRINT,
YOU CAN BE RESPONSIBLE FOR
SENDING A BUNCH OF INNOCENT MEN
INTO DEPRESSION.
- WHY DON'T YOU DO A FAVOR
FOR WORLD PEACE AND DIE ALREADY.
- DON'T YOU SAY
'WORLD PEACE' TO ME.
- ( screaming )
- ( gasps ) NO WAY.
MAYBE THAT WAS A LITTLE MUCH?
- BYE, CATCH YOU LATER.
- UH, HO. YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS.
- WELL, THAT TOOK UP
WAY TOO MUCH TIME.
- Suwano: TREASURE YOUR
FRIENDS. REMEMBER THE CHARACTER
FOR THE WORD "PERSON"
LOOKS LIKE,
TWO PEOPLE LEANING
ON EACH OTHER FOR SUPPORT.
- I GET WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
BUT THAT FREAK WILL
NEVER BE MY FRIEND.
- KILLING, KILLING WILL HAPPEN.
- MAYBE I SHOULD THINK ABOUT
THIS WHOLE "FRIENDS" THING.
I'VE HAD SEVERAL GUYS WHO
I LET SAY WE'RE FRIENDS
IN EXCHANGE FOR FAVORS.
ALL THE GIRLS I KNOW ARE
JEALOUS HAGS. WHO NEEDS THAT?
I GUESS I'M JUST NOT
A "FRIENDS" KINDA GIRL?
- Ai: OMG, WHY DON'T
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I'M WORRIED ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, YOU AIN'T
GOT A BOYFRIEND,
YOU AIN'T GOT A SOCIAL LIFE.
- WAIT A MO, A BOYFRIEND?
I THINK I COULD TOTALLY
HANDLE ONE OF THOSE.
IT'D BE LIKE HAVING THE HOTTEST
PAIR OF SHOES EVER.
PROBLEM IS I'M STUCK
IN A DISCOUNT STORE,
AND THIS IS
A DESIGNER-BRAND-ONLY-ZONE.
- ( thudding )
- ( all exclaim )
- WHAT THE CRAP?
SOME PEOPLE'S CHILDREN, I SWEAR.
REALLY? THAT DUDE'S BEEN
ASLEEP SINCE EPISODE ONE.
I'VE NEVER EVEN SEEN HIS FACE.
- ( gasps )
- ( gasps ) EW, CREEPY TOWN.
- UH, YEAH.
CAN I WARM UP YOUR
BENTO BOX FOR YOU?
- HUH?
- DO YOU NEED CHOPSTICKS
OR A LASER GUN?
- SO IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE,
BUT I SUDDENLY HAVE THIS
STRONG, INTENSE,
HOWEVER, RANDOM, NEED TO LET
SLEEPY PANTS BE MY PRINCE.
SUWANO, I TOTALLY GET
WHAT YOU MEAN NOW
ABOUT THE TWO LINES IN
THE WORD "PERSON"
LEANING ON EACH
OTHER FOR SUPPORT
AND I'VE FOUND IT.
- THAT'S CALLED "USING,"
NOT SUPPORTING.
- THIS POVERTY GOD
ITEM IS CALLED
DEVIL OF THE EARTH'S EARS.
WHOEVER WEARS IT CAN NOT ONLY
HEAR SOMEONE FROM
REALLY FAR AWAY,
BUT THEY CAN ALSO HEAR
THE VOICES IN THEIR MINDS,
WHICH ISN'T ALWAYS A GOOD THING.
- ( yawning loudly )
- HEY THERE.
YOU COME HERE OFTEN?
WHERE THE HELL DID HE GO?
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO HAVE A TALK.
OH, HE LEFT HIS I.D. HERE.
KEITA TSUWABUKI, HUH?
AND WHAT A COINCIDENCE. HE LIVES
RIGHT DOWN THE STREET FROM ME.
THIS IS PERFECT.
- WHAT A KIND PERSON
YOU ARE TO DROP THIS OFF.
- SHE'S NOT ONLY BEAUTIFUL,
SHE'S THOUGHTFUL, TOO.
- WHY DON'T YOU STAY
AND HAVE DINNER WITH US?
- OUR SON'S SO LUCKY
TO HAVE MET AN ANGEL LIKE YOU.
- ( all laughing )
- THIS IS EXACTLY
WHAT WE NEEDED.
A LITTLE LOVE STORY TO BALANCE
OUT ALL THE SLAPSTICK,
MAKES THIS SHOW
WAY MORE REALISTIC
WHO CARES IF IT REQUIRES
MAXIMUM HAPPINESS ENERGY.
- ( laughing )
- REALLY? THIS IS MY LIFE?
- THIS CAN'T BE THE
RIGHT ADDRESS.
NO ONE WOULD CHOOSE
TO LIVE HERE.
I CAN FEEL MY FACE BREAKING OUT
JUST LOOKING AT IT.
- HELP YOU FIND SOMETHING?
- ( gasps )
- OKAY, THIS IS WEIRD.
- AREN'T YOU THAT TIGHTWAD CHICK
FROM MY CLASS?
WHAT WAS YOUR NAME AGAIN?
STARTED WITH A 'K', DIDN'T IT?
OR WAS IT A "C".
- NO! IT'S ICHIKO SAKURA.
SO, YEAH, I FOUND THIS
BY YOUR DESK BEFORE I LEFT.
TSUWABUKI, RIGHT?
- YEAH, YOU CAME ALL THE WAY OUT
HERE JUST TO RETURN THIS TO ME?
THANK YOU. THAT'S SO...
- SELFLESS AND GOOD
SAMARITAN-LY? I KNOW, RIGHT?
- YEAH. SO, I GUESS
I SHOULD DO SOMETHING
TO REPAY YOU FOR THIS, HUH?
YOU WANNA STAY
AND HAVE DINNER WITH US?
- YEAH, OKAY.
CHANGE OF PLANS.
I OFFICIALLY NO LONGER CARE
ABOUT HIS GROSS HOUSE.
HE'S HOT AND WE'RE CLEARLY
ABOUT TO FALL IN LOVE.
- HOW'S IT GOING, GUYS?
- Mika: YAY, YOU'RE BACK.
- Rika: WELCOME HOME.
- WHOA, IS THAT YOUR
NEW GIRLFRIEND, KEITA?
SHE'S SO PRETTY.
- HI, KEITA'S GIRLFRIEND.
DO YOU PLAY D AND D?
- UM. WE'RE HAPPY
TO HAVE YOU. WELCOME.
- WHAT THE HELL? HOW
MANY PEOPLE LIVE HERE?
- THAT TOOK FOREVER. HOW FAR DID
YOU HAVE TO GO TO GET SOY SAUCE?
- FELT LIKE EGYPT, BUT THEY WERE
SELLING IT CHEAP AT THE MARKET.
- ( chuckles awkwardly )
- All: THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD.
- RYUTA, I SAW THAT.
YOU JUST GRABBED THREE PICKLES.
- WE'RE ONLY SUPPOSED
TO GET TWO. NO FAIR.
- YOU MUSTA MISUNDERSTOOD.
YOU ONLY GET TWO.
- WHY ME? YOU'RE A PICKLE-THIEF.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- AND FOR THE LAST TIME,
DO NOT POINT YOUR CHOPSTICKS
AT OTHER PEOPLE.
YOU'RE BOTH BEING
VERY RUDE TO OUR GUEST.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT. I HOPE
YOU'RE ENJOYING YOUR MEAL.
- ( chuckles awkwardly )
- WHY DO I FEEL LIKE
I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE?
- ( whistles )
- EMERGENCY MEETING.
TO DATE OR NOT TO DATE.
THERE AREN'T MANY OPTIONS,
SO THE FACT THAT HE'S HOT
SHOULD COUNT FOR SOMETHING.
- WE NEED TO TAKE
INTO CONSIDERATION
THE INCONVENIENCE
AND AWKWARDNESS,
THAT COMES WITH DATING
A GUY WHO HAS KIDS.
I MEAN THEY'RE NOT HIS, BUT HE'S
OBVIOUSLY RESPONSIBLE FOR THEM.
- WHICH MEANS, WHEREVER WE GO,
THEY WON'T BE TOO FAR BEHIND.
- YOU MEAN, EVEN ON DATES?
WAIT, THEY'D HAVE FRONT ROW
SEATS TO OUR FIRST KISS.
- LET'S PUT IT TO A VOTE.
- All: NOT TO DATE.
- IT'S UNANIMOUS.
THE DECISION IS NOT TO DATE.
- INFORMATION PROCESSED.
HMM, AT LEAST HE'S STILL PRETTY.
SO, ARE YOUR FOLKS
STILL AT WORK OR SOMETHING?
THEIR BOSS MUST BE A JERK
KEEPING THEM THIS LATE.
- THEY RAN OFF.
- HUH?
- OUR FAMILY WAS IN SOME
SERIOUS DEBT.
SO THEY TOOK OFF ONE NIGHT
SAYING THEY WERE GONNA HUNT
FOR BURIED TREASURE
TO TAKE CARE OF IT.
- BUT THEY NEVER CAME BACK HOME.
- HUH. SOUNDS SO LEGIT, TOO.
- AND EVER SINCE THEN
I'VE HAD TO TAKE ON SEVERAL
DIFFERENT JOBS.
BUT AT LEAST THEY'RE NOT
HUNGRY ANYMORE.
- SO, THAT MUST BE WHY
YOU'RE ALWAYS ASLEEP IN CLASS?
- I WORK THE ZOMBIE SHIFT.
- STILL, I DON'T
MIND BEING TIRED.
KNOWING THEY'RE TAKEN CARE OF
MAKES IT WORTH IT.
- YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HUH.
- I'M JUST MOVED BY
THIS "POOR MAN'S LAMENT."
YOU'RE A BETTER
PERSON THAN I AM.
THERE'S NO WAY I WOULD
EVER LIVE LIKE THIS.
- IT'S NOT AS BAD AS YOU THINK.
REALIZING YOU DON'T
NEED MONEY TO BE HAPPY
IS A GREAT WAY TO LIVE.
WE ALL HAVE
A SENSE OF HUMOR ABOUT IT,
AND THE STRUGGLE'S ACTUALLY
BROUGHT US CLOSER TOGETHER.
- I CAN DEFINITELY TELL
YOU GUYS ARE CLOSE.
BUT I DON'T BUY THAT YOU'RE
FINE NOT HAVING MONEY
AND THAT IT WOULDN'T
MAKE YOU HAPPIER.
- ( sighs )
- IT WOULD BE EASIER, OF COURSE,
BUT THERE ARE THINGS THAT
ARE MORE IMPORTANT TO ME.
- OKAY, FINE. LIKE WHAT?
- YEAH, I'M PRETTY MUCH OVER
TALKING ABOUT THIS WITH YOU.
- TRANSLATION, "YOU'RE RIGHT
AND I DON'T WANNA ADMIT IT
'CAUSE I'VE GOT GUY-PRIDE".
IF YOU HAD MONEY, YOU'D
HAVE A HOUSE BIG ENOUGH
FOR ALL TWENTY OF YOU.
AND YOU COULD AFFORD
BETTER FOOD. AM I RIGHT?
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
YOU'VE GOTTA BE THE RUDEST
PERSON I'VE EVER MET.
WHAT ARE YOU SO ANGRY ABOUT?
OR ARE YOU SOME KIND OF PSYCHO?
- OH, NOW WHO'S BEING RUDE?
YOU SOUND LIKE THE
FREAKING POVERTY GOD.
- WHAT DID YOU CALL ME?
- FINE, THEN, HEADS UP.
- LET'S SEE WHAT KIND
OF HAPPINESS MONEY CAN BUY.
YOU CAN USE IT FOR WHATEVER YOU
WANT AND I PROMISE I WON'T TELL.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE. YOU CAN
BUY SOMETHING WAY BETTER
THAN THAT GUNK YOU ATE TONIGHT.
- YAY.
- HEY, HOW MUCH DO
YOU THINK THAT IS?
- DON'T EITHER OF YOU
TOUCH THAT. IT'S NOT OURS.
I THINK IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO.
- IT'S OKAY, RIKA.
- I APOLOGIZE, ICHIKO.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- AND I WANT TO APOLOGIZE
TO ALL OF YOU, TOO.
THIS IS MY FAULT, I'M SORRY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE INVITED HER IN.
- ( grunting )
- GET OUT OF HERE
AND TAKE THAT WITH YOU.
- ( crying )
- KEITA'S MAD.
- IDIOT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT A BUTTHOLE
YOU JUST MADE
YOURSELF OUT TO BE?
- SHUT UP, POVERTY JERK.
- Ryuta: HOW DID SHE GET HERE?
- WHATEVER. I'M OUT. I DON'T
WANNA BE HERE ANYMORE, ANYWAY.
UGH, WHAT IS WRONG
WITH THAT LOSER?
- (yells ) WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THAT PSYCHO BEAST?
- JUST SAYING. THAT'S WHAT
I'D BE THINKING RIGHT NOW
IF I WAS HIM.
DID YOU SEE WHAT HE WAS TRYING
TO MAKE ME EAT FOR DINNER?
UGH. IT'S A LITTLE SAD
HOW CONTENT YOU PRETEND TO BE
WITH THE BITTER, ANGRY TROLL
YOU ARE ON THE INSIDE,
BECAUSE I KNOW YOU'D LIKE
TO GROW A HUMAN SOUL ONE DAY.
- LET ME DRY YOUR EYES.
WHAT OTHER PEARLS OF
WISDOM DO YOU HAVE?
- I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR THEM!
- THAT'S ALL I GOT FOR NOW.
- REALLY SORRY, BABE, I GOT A
JOB TO DO AND UNFORTUNATELY,
THAT DOESN'T INCLUDE
PERSONAL THERAPY SESSIONS
FOR YOUR FAKE LOVE LIFE.
- IT'S NOT FAKE. WHY IS EVERYONE
IN SUCH A BAD MOOD TODAY?
- Woman: LOOK AT THOSE CLOUDS.
WE BETTER GET HOME.
- YEAH, KINDA LOOKS LIKE
THERE'S A TYPHOON ON THE WAY.
- UGH. I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
TURD IS STILL GETTING TO ME.
THIS IS TOTALLY
RUINING MY DAY OFF.
- LOOK, THERE'S
THE PSYCHO BEAST.
- HUH? IT'S TSUWABUKI'S
HOUSE BRAT.
- MY BROTHER TOLD ME PEOPLE LIKE
YOU WHO WORSHIP MONEY ARE CRAZY,
AND WILL NEVER HAVE ANY FRIENDS
UNLESS YOU BUY THEM.
SO, WE ALL CALL YOU
THE PSYCHO BEAST.
- THAT'S CUTE AND ALL, BUT I DO
HAVE A NAME. IT'S ICHIKO SAKURA.
- YEAH, AND THEY
ALL CALL YOU THAT
BECAUSE YOUR JUGS
ARE SO ENORMOUS.
- I SAID ICHIKO,
NOT "TIT-CHIKO",
YOU PERVERTED LITTLE BRAT.
I'M GONNA GRIND THAT NAME
OUT OF YOUR MEMORY.
- AW MAN, I HAVE
THIS ONE ALREADY.
- HEY! DON'T THROW IT AWAY.
I'LL TAKE IT!
- RIGHT. YOU SHOULD TRY TO BUY
YOUR OWN ONCE IN A WHILE.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY CARDS YOU
HAVEN'T MOOCHED OFF OTHER KIDS?
- YES, IT'S PERFECT.
I GET THE SIBS ON
MY SIDE TELLING HIM
WHAT A HORRIBLE
MISTAKE HE'S MADE,
AND THEN HE'LL BE AT MY FEET
BEGGING FOR FORGIVENESS.
OH, DON'T BE SILLY.
WHY DON'T YOU LET YOUR BIG
SISTER HOOK YOU UP?
- WHAT? YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
I DIDN'T ASK YOU
TO BUY ME THOSE.
- COME ON, JUST OPEN IT
AND CHECK THEM OUT.
IF THE CARDS SUCK, THROW THEM
AWAY. IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
- ( gasps )
- WHOA, THAT'S AWESOME. YOU
GOT ONE OF THE SUPER-RARE ONES.
- YEAH, IN YOUR
FIRST PACK, EVEN.
- AREN'T YOU GLAD YOU TOOK
A RISK AND OPENED IT?
- THAT'S WHAT WE CALL
HAPPINESS ENERGY AT WORK, FOLKS.
- THANKS A LOT. UM,
THAT WAS REALLY COOL OF YOU.
- ( smirks ) NOT WHAT YOU EXPECT
FROM A PSYCHO BEAST, IS IT?
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I WAS TOLD THAT WHENEVER
ANYONE DOES SOMETHING NICE
THAT YOU SHOULD SAY THANK YOU,
NO MATTER WHO THEY ARE.
SO, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE
REALLY A PSYCHO OR NOT,
BUT I WANTED TO BE POLITE.
- ( chuckles ) IT'S OKAY.
I ACCEPT YOUR APOLOGY.
- I DIDN'T APOLOGIZE,
BUT, THANKS, TIT-CHIKO!
- ( yells ) WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
MY NAME IS ICHIKO!
- ( screaming )
- LOOK AT ALL THOSE POWERS.
- LET ME SEE IT AGAIN.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW
MANY PACKS I'VE BOUGHT
LOOKING FOR THAT ONE.
- NOT EXACTLY
THE PRIMARY TARGET,
BUT IT DID KINDA FEEL GOOD
TO HELP HIM OUT, I GUESS.
I'M COOL WITH THAT.
- EVEN CRAZY TIT-CHIKO
HAS A GOOD SIDE.
( gasps ) WHAT AM I
GOING TO TELL KEITA?
I CAN'T TELL HIM THE PSYCHO
HAG BOUGHT IT FOR ME.
HE'LL BE PISSED. HUH.
- AH, PLEASE DON'T FALL DOWN
IN THERE. NO.
UGH, I HATE MY LIFE.
THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GONNA FIND IT.
IT'S TOO DARK. AND IT SMELLS!
- WELL, THAT CAN'T BE SAFE.
WOW, I GUESS THEY MUST BE DOING
SOME WORK IN THE SEWERS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
I ACTUALLY FOUND IT.
I'LL JUST WIPE IT OFF
AND IT'LL BE GOOD AS NEW.
- ( exclaims ) OH MY GOSH.
SOMEONE CLOSED IT?
- Tsuwabuki: I'M HOME.
WHAT'S UP WITH ALL THIS RAIN?
- HEY, UH, RYU'S GONE
AND I CAN'T REACH HIM ON
HIS CELL PHONE.
I'VE CALLED ALL OF HIS FRIENDS
AND NO ONE HAS HEARD ANYTHING.
IT'S GETTING LATE. I'M WORRIED.
- ME TOO.
- I WISH KEITA WAS HERE.
THIS IS SO SCARY.
- ( screams ) RYUTA, CAN YOU
HEAR ME? RYUTA, WHERE ARE YOU?
THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOMEONE ELSE I CAN CALL.
SOMEONE HAS TO KNOW WHERE HE
IS. THIS IS CRAZY.
- ( gasps ) SPEAKING OF CRAZY...
- ( door bell ringing )
- IS SOMEONE SERIOUSLY
AT MY DOOR THIS LATE?
HUH? NO WAY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU LOOK LIKE A DROWNED RAT.
- I'M TRYING TO FIND MY BROTHER.
I THOUGHT HE MIGHT'VE COME HERE.
- WELL, YOU THOUGHT WRONG.
HEY, DON'T WORRY ABOUT THANKING
ME FOR THE CARD.
- HUH? WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
DID HE ASK YOU TO BUY ONE OF
THOSE CARD PACKETS FOR HIM?
- OF COURSE NOT. I OFFERED.
- HOW MUCH WAS IT?
- THREE HUNDRED YEN.
- ( sighs ) THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I COULD'VE JUST BOUGHT
THAT FOR HIM MYSELF.
- IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE
MORE THAN JUST A BIG BROTHER
TO THESE GUYS.
- HUH? MAYBE SO.
I HATE TO ADMIT IT, BUT A LOT
OF WHAT YOU SAID MADE SENSE.
I JUST WISH I COULD
GIVE THEM MORE.
THE ONE THING RYU WANTS MORE
THAN ANYTHING IS TO PLAY SOCCER.
BUT I CAN'T AFFORD THE CLUB
FEES, THE BALL, ANY OF IT.
INSTEAD HE PLAYS
USED VIDEO GAMES.
I WISH I COULD BUY
RIKA HER OWN DESK,
SO SHE WOULDN'T HAVE TO STUDY
IN THE KITCHEN.
IT'D BE NICE IF MIKA AND SORATA
DIDN'T HAVE TO WEAR
HAND-ME-DOWNS.
I'M NOT SAYING WE NEED
A CRAP-TON OF MONEY
IN ORDER TO BE HAPPY.
BUT NOT HAVING ANY OF IT
MAKES THINGS SO HARD!
- ASK YOUR FRIENDS FOR HELP.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE.
- WELL, IT ISN'T THAT EASY
FOR ME TO DO.
- WHY NOT?
- I WANNA SHOW MY SIBLINGS
THAT THEY DON'T NEED TO BE
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE
TO HAVE A QUALITY LIFE.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH HAVING TO WORK
FOR EVERYTHING YOU HAVE.
IF THEY LEARN TO RELY
ON THEMSELVES,
THEY CAN'T BE LET DOWN.
BESIDES, YOU'RE THE LAST PERSON
I'D ASK FOR HELP.
- ( swishing )
- OH, GREAT. GO ON AND LECTURE
ME AND MAKE ME FEEL EVEN WORSE.
- THAT'S NOT WHY I'M HERE.
- THEN PLEASE ENLIGHTEN ME.
HEY, WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
AND WHAT DID YOU PUT ON MY HEAD?
- LISTEN CAREFULLY.
- HUH? I'M LOST. LISTEN TO WHAT?
- Ryuta: HELP ME!
- Momiji: RYUTA IS TRAPPED
IN A PRETTY TIGHT SPOT.
YOU'LL NEED TO FOLLOW HIS VOICE.
- ALMOST.
( screams )
- ( exclaims ) RYU.
- I KNOW THIS IS GOING
TO BLOW YOUR MIND,
BUT THE LOUDER HIS VOICE
SOUNDS IN YOUR EAR,
THE CLOSER YOU ARE TO HIM.
- YEAH, I FIGURED
THAT MUCH. THANKS.
- ONE MORE THING.
REMEMBER THIS?
- ( gasps ) I THINK SO.
- CHECK IT OUT.
THIS IS THE POINT OF OUR CHAT.
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU, YOU
COULD SAVE THAT BOY'S LIFE
BY USING YOUR OWN
HAPPINESS ENERGY?
YOU WOULD HAVE TO
GIVE IT AWAY FREELY
BECAUSE YOU WANTED TO HELP,
NOT BECAUSE YOU'RE
EXPECTING TO GET SOMETHING.
IF A MIRACLE HAPPENS
AND YOU PULL THAT OFF,
I'LL HAVE EFFECTIVELY
DONE MY JOB.
OH, WELL.
YOU'VE ALREADY MADE
IT PERFECTLY CLEAR
THAT NO ONE ELSE MATTERS TO YOU
EXCEPT SUWANO.
ME AND MY DUMB IDEAS.
- THANKS A LOT. UM,
THAT WAS REALLY COOL OF YOU.
- NICE TRY. BUT YOU'RE
NOT GONNA GUILT ME
INTO FEELING BAD
ABOUT WHAT I SAID.
- NAH, YOU HAD A PRETTY DECENT
POINT ABOUT THE POWER OF CASH.
- THEY'RE WRONG ABOUT ME.
I WANTED THEM TO REGRET
WHAT THEY SAID.
- LOOKS LIKE THIS IS
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY, THEN.
- SCREW IT. I DON'T NEED TO
RISK CARING ABOUT ANYONE ELSE.
- SO YOU'RE GONNA
LEAVE HIM OUT THERE?
PLEASE. YOU'RE NOT THAT CRUEL.
RYUTA ISN'T JUST ANYONE ELSE
AND YOU KNOW IT.
- FINE. BUT CAN I TELL YOU
SOMETHING?
- ( screams ) TAKING ORDERS FROM
YOU KINDA REALLY TICKS ME OFF!
- AW, POOR BABY.
KILLING.
THAT'S WHAT WE CALL
A "WHACK JOB".
- YEAH, PEOPLE FOR THE MOST
PART ARE DESPICABLE CREATURES.
BUT STILL. ONCE IN A WHILE
THEY SURPRISE ME.
- RYU, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- Ryuta: I'M OVER HERE.
- WHAT THE...
YOU IDIOT. DON'T MOVE, I'LL
BE RIGHT THERE. JUST HOLD ON.
- ( whimpering )
- HERE, GRAB MY HAND.
COME ON, REACH.
- ( gasps )
- ( screams )
- ( screams ) RYU! ICHIKO?
- ( panting )
- AM I REALLY DOING THIS?
I CAN'T BELIEVE I WILLINGLY TOOK
ORDERS FROM THAT POVERTY CREEP.
THIS KID ISN'T WORTH IT.
HE'S NOT WORTH IT.
DAMN IT, HAPPINESS ENERGY,
YOU HAVE TO SAVE THIS BOY!
- ( panting )
- YOU SAVED ME, TIT-CHIKO.
- ICHIKO!
- YOU'RE SAFE.
- I'M SORRY!
- ( crying )
- WHAT THE HELL'S WRONG
WITH YOU? WHAT HAPPENED?
- I DROPPED MY CARD.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO!
- Ichiko: I GET IT.
- THE TWO LINES IN "PERSON."
- ICHIKO?
- ARE YOU INSANE?
YOU COULD'VE HURT YOURSELF.
I MEAN, YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU EVEN SURVIVED THAT JUMP.
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING INSANE?
YOU WERE ABOUT TO DO
THE EXACT SAME THING.
I JUST DID IT FIRST.
AND P.S. WHAT IF SOMETHING
WENT WRONG ON THE WAY DOWN?
THEN YOU'D BOTH BE DEAD.
- YEAH, I KNOW. BUT YOU RISKED
YOUR WHOLE LIFE FOR US.
- NO WAY, NOTHING WAS GONNA
HAPPEN TO ME.
- WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
WAIT UP A SECOND.
THANK YOU. I WISH I COULD
REPAY YOU.
I'M SORRY ABOUT WHAT I SAID.
I WAS WRONG ABOUT YOU.
HEY, GET UP HERE
AND TELL HER THANK YOU.
YOU'D BE DEAD RIGHT NOW
IF IT WASN'T FOR HER.
- UM, I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THANK YOU, TIT-CHIKO!
- ICHIKO.
- SUWANO, I WISH YOU
WERE HERE TO SEE THIS,
BECAUSE IT'S SO
HARD TO DESCRIBE.
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT
MOMENT CHANGED MY LIFE.
NOTHING MATERIAL,
BUT THERE'S A WARMTH IN MY
HEART I'VE NEVER FELT BEFORE.
- ( imitating Suwano ) YOU'RE
GROWING UP, YOUNG ICHIKO.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE
SEEDS OF KINDNESS
ARE SPROUTING IN
YOUR MOSSY SOUL.
OH, AND WHILE WE'RE HERE,
WHY DON'T YOU BE A DEAR AND GIVE
US SOME OF THAT HAPPY JUICE?
- ( screams ) I GIVE AND I GIVE
AND I GIVE AND EVERY SINGLE TIME
YOU BREAK ALL MY GEAR
FOR NO REASON.
THIS IS WHY WE CAN'T
HAVE NICE THINGS.
DO YOU KNOW HOW
MUCH MY STUFF COSTS!
I'M NOT GETTING REIMBURSED HERE.
- I'M NOT GETTING REIMBURSED
FOR THE LOSS OF MENTAL STABILITY
CAUSED BY YOUR CONSTANT NAGGING.
- DON'T EVEN TRY TO BLAME
YOUR INSTABILITIES ON ME.
THAT'S WHAT GOT US
INTO THIS MESS.
- IT'S THAT CLUMSY LITTLE
BRAT THAT GOT US HERE.
I KNEW THERE WAS A REASON
I NEVER LIKED HIM.
- WHAT? YOU FAKER! WHY DID
I EVEN THINK FOR A MOMENT
THERE WAS ANYTHING PULSING
INSIDE OF YOU EXCEPT TAR?
- WHAT AM I, A ROBOT NOW?
- Students: THIS WEEK'S...
- Nadeshiko: "OH, NADESHIKO!"
- CHECK IT OUT. I'VE HAD
GREAT SCENES THIS WEEK.
AT LEAST THREE, AND I'M
NOT SURE IF YOU'VE NOTICED,
BUT I'VE BEEN GETTING A LOT MORE
SCREEN TIME IN OTHER EPISODES
AND FOR SOME REASON
THIS ONE JUST--