- ( humming )
- THESE CREPES ARE HARD TO GET.
THEY ONLY MAKE TEN A DAY.
AND THIS ONE IS ALL MINE.
- Girl: GET OUT OF MY WAY.
- THAT HURT.
- OW.
- HEY, COME ON, WE GOT TO GO.
- DON'T MOVE.
- ( gasps )
- CATCH YOU LATER, ALLIGATOR.
- HEY, COME BACK HERE.
- OH, NO, WHERE'S MY CREPE?
HAPPINESS ENERGY
IS STILL WORKING.
- YEAH, WHAT?
- DROP THE ATTITUDE, MISS.
- SHOPLIFTER.
- SHOPLIFTER?
- I'M GONNA HAVE
TO TAKE YOU DOWNTOWN.
- HUH? YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
YOU'RE GONNA RUIN MY
HAPPY MOMENT RIGHT NOW,
AND I DIDN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING.
- CALM DOWN OR I'M GONNA HAVE TO
BOOK YOU FOR RESISTING ARREST.
- YOU STUPID JERK.
- Ranmaru: HOLD ON.
- BEFORE YOU GO AROUND
PREACHING ABOUT HAPPINESS,
IT MIGHT DO YOU SOME GOOD
TO TAKE A LOOK IN THE MIRROR.
GIRLS SHOULD NEVER RAISE
THEIR FISTS IN ANGER.
ESPECIALLY IF HAPPINESS
IS WHAT THEY'RE AFTER.
WHERE ANGER THRIVES,
HAPPINESS IS ABSENT,
I GUESS NOBODY
EVER TOOK THE TIME
TO TEACH YOU THAT, LITTLE GIRL.
- WHAT?
- WHO'S THAT?
- SHE ISN'T YOUR FRIEND?
- NO, I DON'T KNOW
THAT GIRL, I SWEAR...
IT WAS ME, OFFICERS, I CONFESS.
IT'S TRUE, I SHOPLIFTED.
- BUT NOT BECAUSE I WANTED TO,
I TOLD HER NO BUT SHE
WOULDN'T LISTEN.
SHE SAID SHE'D HURT ME IF I
DIDN'T DO WHAT SHE ORDERED.
- HMM.
- DID YOU PUT HER UP TO THIS?
- THAT'S LOW.
- WAIT, YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
- ARREST HER RIGHT NOW.
- ( screams )
- WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO ASK YOU
A COUPLE OF QUESTIONS, MISS.
HEY, WHERE'D SHE GO?
- DAMN, I'LL MAKE HER PAY.
I'LL TEACH HER TO MESS WITH ME.
- DELISH.
- I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED
TO THAT GIRL I GOT INTO IT WITH.
I BET SHE WAS SUPER PISSED,
OH, WELL. IT'S NOT LIKE
I'LL EVER SEE HER AGAIN.
- ALL RIGHT. THERE'S A
NEW TRANSFER STUDENT
I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO TODAY.
- EXCUSE ME, WHY IS IT WE ALWAYS
HAVE NEW TRANSFER STUDENTS?
- GOOD QUESTION,
IT'S BECAUSE THE MAIN CHARACTER
OF OUR ANIME IS IN THIS CLASS.
- THAT MAKES SENSE.
- ALL RIGHT, SON. COME ON IN.
- ( exclaims )
- MISTER RINDO, YOU PREFER TO BE
CALLED RANMARU, IS THAT RIGHT?
- UH, IT'S MISS RINDO, BUT YEAH,
I PREFER TO BE CALLED RANMARU.
I LOVE KARATE, MY
DREAM IS TO BRING BACK
MY FATHER'S MARTIAL ARTS DOJO,
THAT CLOSED DOWN
AFTER HE WENT BANKRUPT.
- I SEE, IS THIS A SO CALLED
BOY RAISED AS A GIRL PATTERN?
- STOP CALLING ME A
BOY, DOUCHE- BAG,
I MEAN, UNLESS YOU WANT YOUR
FACE BASHED IN.
- SORRY.
- OH, THIS IS NOT GOOD.
THERE'S NO POSSIBLE WAY THIS
GIRL DOESN'T REMEMBER ME,
IS THERE?
WAIT, I'VE GOT IT. I KNOW A WAY
OUT OF THIS, I NEED A DISGUISE.
SHE'LL NEVER RECOGNIZE ME NOW.
- ( chuckles ) IF THIS IS A
COSPLAY CONTEST, YOU'RE TOAST.
- THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOU, POVERTY GOD.
YOU'RE JUST DRAWING
ATTENTION TO US.
- SWEET. I WANT IN ON THIS.
- COME ON, NOT YOU TOO.
- TAKE A SEAT IN THE BACK ROW
NEXT TO THE HALLWAY, PLEASE.
- KAY- O.
- SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT
OVER HERE. HMM?
HEY, YOU'RE THE GIRL
FROM YESTERDAY.
- THIS SUCKS. SHE TOOK
ONE LOOK AND FIGURED IT OUT.
- WE NEED TO TALK.
- SHE'S GONNA MURDER ME.
- HUH?
- MISS ICHIKO,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THE TRANSFER STUDENT GOT
VIOLENT WITH ME OUT OF NOWHERE.
- HUH?
- WHY WOULD YOU DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- WE WON'T STAND FOR
THAT TYPE OF BEHAVIOR, NEWB.
- YEAH, NOT COOL.
- YOU GOT THE WRONG IDEA HERE.
- ( smirks )
- ( grunts ) DAMN YOU.
- I'LL MAKE HER PAY.
BUT THERE'S NO WAY I CAN
GET TO HER AT SCHOOL,
NOT WITH HER IDIOT
BRIGADE AROUND.
- HMM?
- ( chuckles )
- ( door bell rings )
- Ichiko: COMING!
THIS SO ISN'T HAPPENING.
IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
- ( screams )
- I KNOW YOU SAW ME, YOU JERK.
- AND YOU FOUND OUT
WHERE I LIVED, HOW?
- WILL AND DETERMINATION.
- AND A LITTLE BIT OF HELP,
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
I HELD UP MY END OF THE
BARGAIN, NOW GO AHEAD,
AND BASH IN HER STUPID,
HAPPY FACE.
- DAMN YOU, POVERTY GOD,
I'LL MAKE YOU PAY FOR
SELLING ME OUT LIKE THIS.
- HEY, DON'T BLAME THIS
ON HER! IT'S YOUR FAULT,
I CAN'T STAND PEOPLE WHO
DON'T TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THEIR OWN
ACTIONS AND FESS UP
TO THE AWFUL THINGS
THEY'VE DONE.
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A BIG COWARD.
- WELL, AT LEAST I
DON'T GO AROUND
BREAKING DOWN PEOPLE'S DOORS.
- YOU FULL BLOWN NUT- JOB.
- A NUT- JOB?
- COME ON, DON'T LET HER
BEAT YOU, SAY SOMETHING.
- WELL, YOUR BOOBS ARE HUGE.
- YOU COULD'VE BEEN A LITTLE
MEANER, BUT GOOD EFFORT.
- ( chuckles )
THAT'S SWEET OF YOU, BUT WAS
THAT REALLY YOUR COMEBACK?
YOU, MAN- FACED TOM- BOY.
- ( screaming )
- SCREW YOU, GAZONGA GIRL.
- UH- OH.
- ( screams )
- MORON, DID SHE ACTUALLY
THINK SHE COULD WIN THE DAY
AGAINST MY HAPPINESS ENERGY?
- 'E', IT'S FOR EFFORT.
- ( exclaims )
- LISTEN UP, LADY PANTS. YOU'LL
PAY FOR THIS, I PROMISE YOU.
IT IS ON LIKE DONKEY KONG.
YOU VERSUS ME, ONE ON ONE.
- WELL, YOU GONNA FIGHT HER?
- SHE FELL THIRTEEN STORIES,
HOW IS SHE STILL ALIVE?
- Male Student: ICHIKO'S GONNA
BATTLE THE NEW TRANSFER STUDENT.
- CAT FIGHT!
- NOWHERE TO RUN THIS TIME,
IS THERE, COWARD?
- IF ANYBODY SHOULD
BE RUNNING AWAY, IT'S YOU.
- TWO HUNDRED ON ICHIKO.
- RINDO ALL THE WAY.
- COLAS, CANDY, POPCORN,
ICE- COLD BEER!
- DUDE, WE'RE AT SCHOOL,
YOU CAN'T SELL BEER HERE.
- NAH, IT'S COOL, I SAW
OUR TEACHER BUY SOME EARLIER.
- OKAY, THE LOSER OF
THIS MATCH HAS TO DO
WHATEVER THE WINNER
TELLS THEM TO DO.
- THAT'S OKAY BY ME,
JUST BE AWARE, IF I WIN,
I'M GONNA MAKE YOU
LEAVE THIS SCHOOL.
- OH IS THAT SO?
THEN MAY THE BEST GIRL WIN.
I'VE WORKED MY BUTT OFF
TO GET AS STRONG AS I AM.
NO WAY IN HELL, I'LL LET YOU
TAKE THAT AWAY.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY
FOR A BEAT DOWN, LADY PANTS.
'CAUSE GUESS WHAT?
YOU'RE GETTING ONE.
- HMM.
- IT'S THE END OF THE LINE
FOR YOU, GIVE UP RIGHT NOW,
OR FACE MY TERRIBLE WRATH.
LAST CHANCE.
- KILL HER!
- AKANE, YOUR HAIR IS LOOKING
KINDA THROWED.
- SHUT UP!
- ( screams )
- MY EYES.
- DAMN, I'M STUCK.
- OW, OW, YOU WIN.
YOU GOT ME. I GIVE UP, OKAY?
- ( people cheering )
- WOW, I TOTALLY DID IT.
- OH, YEAH, AWESOME. WOO.
- WE LOVE YOU, ICHIKO.
- IT'S OVER ALREADY?
THAT'S SO LAME.
- IT WOULD'VE BEEN WAY COOLER
IF THEY FOUGHT TO THE DEATH.
- OR IF THEY WERE NAKED.
- SO, HOW'D WE DO?
- OVER NINE THOUSAND.
- OUTSTANDING.
- WE'RE GONNA BE FILTHY
STINKING RICH. ( laughs )
- OH, HECK YEAH.
WE ARE EATING OUT TONIGHT.
- THIS SUCKS, HOW COULD
I LOSE TO THAT LITTLE BRAT?
- YO.
- GREAT FIGHT, REAL GOOD STUFF,
YOU GAVE US AN AWESOME
SHOW OUT THERE.
IF YOU EVER DO IT AGAIN, I SURE
HOPE YOU'LL GIVE ME A CALL.
- I'LL BE RICH.
- OH, SURE.
- THANKS SO MUCH, WAIT,
WHAT'S YOUR NAME AGAIN?
- I'M KEITA TSUWABUKI.
- AND MY NAME'S MOMIJI.
- NOT YOU.
- SO COOL.
- I HATE TO INTERRUPT.
- ( gasps )
- BUT YOU DO REMEMBER,
WHAT I SAID ABOUT WHAT YOU'D
HAVE TO DO IF YOU LOST, RIGHT?
- YES, I REMEMBER.
A PROMISE IS A PROMISE,
I'LL GET OUT OF YOUR HAIR.
- AND SO, THE TOM- BOY,
KARATE- LOVING,
FREAK- SHOW PSYCHOPATH
VANISHED FROM MY SIGHT FOREVER.
- Teacher: WE HAVE A
NEW TRANSFER STUDENT
THAT I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE
TO YOU TODAY.
- Ichiko: BUT THEN.
SHE CAME BACK!
- THIS IS MISS RINDO,
SHE TRANSFERRED IN,
THEN SHE LEFT,
AND NOW SHE'S BACK.
- I ONLY HAVE ONE PURPOSE HERE.
THAT'S TO DESTROY ICHIKO SAKURA.
- I GUESS I SHOULD'VE BEEN A
LITTLE MORE SPECIFIC
WITH MY REQUEST.
- I'M NOT SURE WHY, BUT I HAVE
A FEELING ME AND THIS GIRL
ARE GONNA GET ALONG JUST FINE.
- Man: HIDEBU.
- Man 2: UWARABA.
- Man 3: ABESHI.
- ARE YOU TWO ALL RIGHT?
- WE'RE FINE, THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR SAVING US.
- DAMN, THESE PUNKS
ARE NO CHALLENGE AT ALL.
- ICHIKO, I'LL GET YOU
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO.
- ( chuckles )
- HERE'S THE DEAL, I WANT
YOU TO FIGHT ME AGAIN.
- WHAT? NO.
- THIS ISN'T AN OPTION, LADY.
YOU AND I ARE GONNA
DO THIS THING.
- WHAT'S YOUR DEAL?
WHAT IS IT ABOUT ME THAT YOU
DON'T LIKE SO MUCH, ANYWAY?
- JUST STOP RIGHT THERE.
- YOU DON'T KNOW WHEN TO QUIT,
DO YOU MISS RINDO?
- WE WON'T LET YOU LAY
ANOTHER HAND ON HER.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU,
WHY ARE YOU SO FREAKING
OBSESSED WITH HER?
- COME ON RANMARU,
TAKE THEM ALL ON AT ONCE.
- HEY, SHUT UP. EVERYBODY
BACK OFF ME RIGHT NOW.
- ALL RIGHT. YOU KIDS
JUST CALM DOWN...
- STOP THIS NONSENSE AT ONCE.
ANY FURTHER CONFRONTATION
WOULD BE POINTLESS.
- BUT, DON'T YOU WORRY,
A REMATCH IS COMING SOON.
- ( students cheering )
- AW, COME ON.
- OH, HELL YEAH.
- YOU DON'T GET TO DECIDE
FOR BOTH OF US.
- GET YOUR TICKETS RIGHT HERE.
- OKAY, THAT'S IT. I'VE HAD IT.
- I'M TRYING TO SLEEP. SHUT UP.
- ( gasps )
- I'M SORRY.
- HE'S RIGHT THOUGH,
WE CAN'T MAKE ALL THIS RACKET IF
HE'S GONNA SLEEP.
- THOSE KIDS NEVER LISTEN
TO WHAT I SAY.
- THIS IS DRIVING ME NUTS.
- ( chuckles )
- I LOVE YOU.
- Nah, I LOVE YOU.
- ( screams )
- MAN, I SHOULDN'T BE
THINKING ABOUT THAT.
I SHOULD BE THINKING
ABOUT
CLOBBERING THE EVER- LOVING
CRAP OUT OF LADY PANTS.
BESIDES,
WHAT WOULD SOMEONE LIKE HIM
SEE IN A TOMBOY LIKE ME?
- WELL, HELLO. HI, THERE.
- ( screams ) NOT COOL, MAN.
NOT COOL.
- DID YOU HEAR THAT?
- OH, YEAH.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU TWO
TALKING ABOUT?
- NOW LISTEN UP, I KNOW
YOU THINK YOU'RE A BOY.
BUT YOU'RE NOT, YOU'RE A GIRL.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU
THINK YOU'RE ABOUT TO DO,
BUT FORGET ABOUT IT.
- Momiji: SOMETIMES,
I DRESS UP ALL SEXY- LIKE,
AND THEN I LIKE TO MAKE OUT
WITH A HANDSOME LOOKING BOY.
- STOP READING MY MIND. I MEAN,
SHUT UP, I'D NEVER SAY THAT.
- IF YOU'LL JUST LET ME,
I CAN HELP YOU OUT.
- WAIT, WHAT? WHY WOULD YOU
DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- OH, DON'T YOU KNOW?
WE HAVE MET ON THE FIELD OF
BATTLE AND FOUGHT TO THE END,
OUR BOND'S THICKER THAN BLOOD,
IT CAN NEVER BE BROKEN.
- WE'RE CONNECTED FOREVER.
- HUH?
JUST LEAVE IT TO ME, I SWEAR,
I WON'T STEER YOU WRONG.
- UH, YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
- GULLIBLE IDIOTS ARE
SO EASY TO MANIPULATE.
NOW, THAT I'VE EARNED HER
TRUST, I CAN GET CLOSE ENOUGH
TO STAB HER IN THE BACK,
AND MAKE THAT TOMBOY
PAY FOR WHAT SHE'S DONE.
- ICHIKO THINKS SHE'S CLEVER,
BUT I SEE THROUGH HER SCHEME.
- RANMARU AND I WILL TEAM UP
AND TAKE HER HAPPINESS ENERGY
AWAY FOREVER.
OH, YES, ICHIKO, YOUR DAY
IS COMING VERY SOON.
- ( people chattering )
- THERE. ALL DONE.
- YOU'RE GORGEOUS, HONESTLY,
IT'S LIKE I'M LOOKING AT A
DIFFERENT PERSON.
- WHOA, IS THAT ME?
- YEP, SO, HOW DOES IT
FEEL TO BE REBORN?
- Both: NO MATTER WHAT, SHE'LL
NEVER LOOK AS GOOD AS I DO.
- WELL, IT'S WEIRD.
- STOP CHEWING ON LEAVES.
- IT'S SO AIRY DOWN THERE.
- STOP PLAYING WITH YOUR SKIRT.
- YEAH, THESE SHOES
ARE KINDA HARD TO WALK IN.
- GET UP, RIGHT NOW.
- AW, MAN, THIS SUCKS.
- WHOA, DUDE,
SHE IS REALLY CUTE.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- ( crying )
- THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
ANYONE'S EVER CALLED ME CUTE.
- NOW, IF YOU CAN JUST LAND A
BOYFRIEND, YOU'LL BE GOOD TO GO.
- A BOYFRIEND?
- WHOA.
- NO WAY, I DON'T THINK
I'M READY FOR THAT.
DRESSING UP LIKE THIS IS ABOUT
ALL I CAN HANDLE AT THE MOMENT.
THANK YOU, BOTH OF YOU.
I WILL NEVER FORGET
WHAT YOU'VE DONE FOR ME TODAY.
- IT MEANS SO MUCH.
- HMM.
- BUT, I GOTTA GO CHANGE.
- HMM?
- IF MY OLD MAN SAW THIS,
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT HE WOULD DO.
- YOUR OLD MAN, HUH?
- HE ALWAYS WANTED A SON TO TAKE
OVER THE DOJO AFTER HE WAS GONE,
BUT IT NEVER HAPPENED.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR HIM, THE ONLY
CHILD HE EVER HAD WAS ME.
SO, HE MADE IT HIS
MISSION TO MAKE ME
THE BEST FEMALE KARATEKA EVER.
- YOU THINK I'M A HOTHEAD,
WAIT TILL YOU MEET HIM.
- SO, IT'S YOUR FATHER'S FAULT
THAT YOU'RE ALL MASCULINE
AND BUTCH LIKE THAT?
- HEY, YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT HIM, OKAY?
I MEAN SURE, HE'S STRICT
WHEN IT COMES TO KARATE,
BUT I RESPECT HIM FOR
BRINGING ME UP ALL ON HIS OWN,
THAT COULDN'T'VE BEEN
AN EASY THING TO DO.
- ( screams )
- WELL, I'LL NEVER GET THAT,
YOU KNOW, BEING ABLE
TO RESPECT YOUR PARENTS.
- WONDER WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
- WHAT?
- I GUESS IT'S PROBABLY TIME
FOR ME TO CHANGE CLOTHES.
- NAH, NOT YET.
I THINK I'LL ENJOY IT
A LITTLE BIT LONGER
BEFORE I HAVE TO GET HOME.
- RANMARU.
- HUH?
- GOOD MORNING, ICHIKO.
- GOOD MORNING, YOU GUYS.
- ( students murmuring )
- WHOA.
- CHECK HER OUT.
- ( gasps )
- HEY, WHERE ARE THE CLOTHES
FROM YESTERDAY?
HOW DID YOU CUT YOUR FACE?
RANMARU, DID YOUR DAD
DO THAT TO YOU?
- MEH, IT'S NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS,
SO WHY DON'T YOU STAY THE
HELL OUT OF IT?
MATTER OF FACT,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST LEAVE
ME ALONE ALL TOGETHER.
- YOU'RE NOT SERIOUSLY
GOING TO HER HOUSE, ARE YOU?
SHE ASKED YOU TO LEAVE
HER ALONE, YOU KNOW?
YOU SHOULDN'T STICK YOUR NOSE
IN OTHER PEOPLE'S BUSINESS,
ESPECIALLY NOT WHEN
IT COMES TO FAMILY.
- HEY, WHO ARE YOU TO TALK,
POVERTY GOD!
- ( grunts )
- GET BACK UP.
YOU'VE DISAPPOINTED ME.
WHEN DID KARATE GET REPLACED
BY NONSENSE LIKE THIS?
I DIDN'T RAISE YOU TO CARE
ABOUT SUPERFICIAL GARBAGE!
- NO, FATHER. PLEASE, I...
- ( gasps )
- HOW CAN YOU EVER HOPE
TO BE A TRUE POWER
IN THE WORLD OF KARATE,
WHEN YOU ALLOW YOUR MIND
TO BE DELUDED BY COMMON TRIFLES?
- HUH?
- IT'S HER.
- IS IT?
- SO, YOU'RE THE YOUNG LADY WHO
DEFEATED MY DAUGHTER, ARE YOU?
- THAT'S RIGHT, AND I'M ALSO
THE ONE WHO DRESSED HER UP
TO MAKE HER LOOK LIKE A GIRL,
IF YOU WANNA KNOW THE TRUTH.
- WHAT?
- I WANT YOU TO LISTEN TO ME,
OF ALL THE STUFF THERE IS
TO LOATHE IN THIS WORLD,
I HATE TWO THINGS THE MOST.
- THE FIRST ONE IS
THE POVERTY GOD.
- HEY.
- YOU KNOW WHAT
THE SECOND ONE IS?
PARENTS WHO FORCE KIDS
TO BE SOMETHING THEY'RE NOT,
SELFISH FATHERS WHO
PUT THEIR OWN NEEDS
BEFORE THEIR CHILDREN.
FIGHT ME RIGHT NOW.
IF I BEAT YOU,
YOU HAVE TO LET HER DO AND
WEAR WHATEVER SHE WANTS,
UNDERSTAND?
- OH, WOW.
- HE'S CLEARLY MUCH STRONGER.
QUESTION IS,
IS THIS AN OPPONENT SHE CAN BEAT
WITH JUST HER HAPPINESS ENERGY?
- THIS IS QUITE A BRAZEN ACT
FOR A YOUNG LADY,
BUT FIGHTING WOMEN AND CHILDREN
GOES AGAINST THE
PRINCIPLES OF MY DOJO.
- CONVENIENT.
- BUT, SEEING AS HOW
YOU'RE A LITTLE BRAT.
- IT'S MY JOB AS AN ADULT
TO PUNISH YOU,
IF I DON'T TEACH YOU
A LESSON, WHO WILL?
I ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE,
DEFEND YOURSELF!
- DON'T DO THIS, FATHER,
LEAVE HER ALONE.
- ( screams )
- DRAGON STRICT KICK, C'YA!
- ( screams ) MY EYES.
- DEJA VU.
- (grunts ) I'M STUCK.
- HUH?
( screams )
- YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A LITTLE GIRL.
DON'T PUSH YOUR LUCK.
- DON'T YOU SEE?
THAT OUTFIT MADE HER SMILE,
SURE, SHE WAS DRESSED UP LIKE A
GIRL, BUT IT MADE HER FEEL GOOD.
YOUR DAUGHTER
WAS SO HAPPY.
WHO ARE YOU
TO TAKE THAT AWAY?
WHO ARE YOU TO DENY
HER HAPPINESS?
- ( screams ) THERE'S NOTHING I
HATE MORE THAN PARENTS LIKE YOU.
HUH? RANMARU? WHY?
- DON'T DO THIS.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S NOT YOUR PLACE,
THE TRUTH IS,
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT HIM.
HE MAY BE THE KIND OF PERSON
YOU HATE AND WANT TO PUNISH.
BUT TO ME, HE'S MY DAD,
AND I LOVE HIM.
SO, PLEASE, PLEASE.
YOU HAVE TO LEAVE US BE.
DON'T HURT HIM, I'M BEGGING YOU.
- I TOLD YOU NOT TO STICK YOUR
NOSE WHERE IT DOESN'T BELONG.
- SHUT UP.
- IF YOU'RE JUST GONNA
LIE THERE AND MOPE,
YOU'LL GET NO PITY FROM ME.
IF MISTER SUWANO WERE HERE,
I BET HE'D CONSOLE YOU
BY TELLING YOU,
YOU WERE DOING THE RIGHT THING.
BUT SINCE HE'S NOT HERE,
I GUESS YOU'RE OUT OF LUCK.
AS IT IS, YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME.
- HUH. FATHER?
- I GOTTA GO.
- HER NAME IS ICHIKO, RIGHT?
- THERE AREN'T VERY MANY
PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD
WHO WOULD STICK THEIR NECK OUT
FOR SOMEONE LIKE THAT, YOU KNOW?
I THINK YOU'VE GOT YOURSELF
A FINE FRIEND THERE.
- OH. ACCEPT,
SHE'S NOT MY FRIEND.
- HE MADE YOU PUT ON
THAT NASTY OUTFIT, HUH?
- NO. IN FACT,
THE OLD MAN TOLD ME
I COULD WEAR WHATEVER I WANT.
BUT TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I THINK I LIKE THIS BETTER.
SORRY ABOUT YESTERDAY,
AND I APPRECIATE ALL YOUR HELP,
BUT I'VE REALIZED I'M HAPPY
JUST THE WAY I AM.
THANK YOU, THOUGH,
AND MY FATHER TOLD ME TO
TELL YOU THANK YOU AS WELL.
- IT'S WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE.
AND HEY, DON'T WORRY, I TOTALLY
WASN'T TRYING TO SCREW YOU OVER.
- WHAT'S UP WITH HER?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO TELL
YOU, THAT'S JUST HOW SHE IS.
- Ichiko: 'CAUSE GUESS WHAT?
IT'S ICHIKO FESTIVAL TIME.
♪ FOR SHE'S A JOLLY GOOD FELLOW,
FOR SHE'S A JOLLY GOOD FELLOW ♪
♪ FOR SHE'S
A JOLLY GOOD FELLOW ♪
- Students: THIS WEEK'S.
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO.
- I'M SO SORRY TO KEEP YOU
WAITING, BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE.
DID YOU SEE ME AGAIN THIS WEEK?
NOT EVERYTHING IN THIS CRAZY
WORLD LASTS FOREVER,
BUT MY EXPLOITS CONTINUE
EVER ON IN GLORY.
HERE'S WHAT I WAS UP TO
THIS WEEK, FOLKS.
AND THEN I WENT OVER HERE,
AS WELL, BUT JUST FOR THIS WEEK,
THERE'S A SPECIAL EXTRA!
- Students: EPISODE 1'S.
- Nadeshiko: OH, SUKENO.
- AT THE REQUEST
OF SOME OF YOU, FANS,
WE'RE GOING TO PLAY BACK
THE SCENE IN EPISODE ONE
WHERE THE ORIGINAL AUTHOR
APPEARED IN THE SHOW.
SO, HERE IT IS.
- WHAT THE...
- NOW WASN'T THAT
SOMETHING, PEOPLE?
LET'S PLAY IT AGAIN,
JUST FOR FUN.
- WHAT THE...
- ONE LAST TIME, WITH THE
AUTHOR'S SELF PORTRAIT.
- WHAT THE...
- ( laughs )