And I really didn't want
to get out of bed this morning.
Ditto, but at least we get
to work out in the pool!
I know!
Wait, hold on, a rifle Blaze?
Are you sure you didn't mistake
what you saw?
I'm sure. Her Blaze
was definitely a rifle.
[gunshot]
But, Tor, how can that be?
A Blaze can't manifest as any
weapon with a complex structure.
Well, I guess it actually can
if you're an Exception,
like she is.
--Huh?
--An "Exception"?
I'd let her explain,
but it looks like Lilith
might not be joining us today.
[LILITH] The Exception
and the Irregular.
Seems we're fated
to be together.
Both you and me, Tor.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Man, oh man, so that's
the power of a Level 2, huh?
That Tomoe chick is
on a whole other level!
We're all gonna have
to try harder, you guys!
Right!
Level 2, eh? So that's what
the Rite of Sublimation does.
[TOR]
I didn't feel any different
after the new Lukifer
was injected.
[grunts]
[STUDENTS shout]
Oh! But I guess
it actually does give you
a whole lot more speed and power
than you had beforehand.
--[MIYABI panting]
--Huh?
Hey, way to go!
--Looks like you're in the lead!
--Huh?
Wow, I guess I am!
That's never happened
to me before!
Then double congrats,
Miyabi! Here.
Uhh... oh, thanks.
--[grunts]
--Oh.
[chuckles] You know,
I probably only did well
because you've been cheering
me on, Tor. So thank you.
I didn't have
anything to do with it.
You're the one
who's been working so hard.
Hm-mm. No, not really.
Um. I'd say it's all because
of your encouragement.
No. It's because
of you, Miyabi. He's right.
I guess, maybe?
To Sublimate, your physical
and spiritual strength
have to match your new level,
so stop being so humble, okay?
You should
be proud of it, Miyabi.
Yes, exactly, just like
you girls should be proud
of your pert, young breasts
that all the boys keep ogling!
[giggles]
Isn't that right, Tor?
Wait, what are
you asking me for?
Because you were!
And you're even doing it again
right now, aren't you? [cries]
You're a perv and a dog!
[TOR]
You've got the wrong idea!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[inhales]
--Nice! I expected nothing less.
--[grunts]
--Why hasn't she come up yet?
--Hmm?
Is something wrong? Is she okay?
[pants] Julie!
[STUDENTS murmur]
I'm sorry.
You see, we don't really swim
all that much
back home in Gimle.
I thought I could just imitate
what I saw the rest
of you do, but...
I never saw that coming.
Wow. Julie is actually bad
at something.
[chuckles]
Well, like people say,
there's a first time
for everything.
I think you should take it easy
for the rest of the day,
all right, Julie?
Ja.
You're soaking wet, Julie.
You don't want to catch a cold.
Thanks, Tor.
[chuckles] Tora.
Do you wanna see
who can swim faster?
[chuckles]
Bring it on, buddy!
[sighs]
I bet if I didn't know
how to swim,
he'd pay attention to me.
Tor, do you think you could
teach me how to swim sometime?
Yeah, no problem.
We'll look at the calendar
and get it scheduled, 'kay?
Uhh... you go on ahead,
and I'll catch up later!
Um, Tor?
Another
outstanding blend, Sarah.
You are most gracious.
--[TOR] What are you doing?
--[BOTH] Hmm?
Can't you tell, Tor?
I'm enjoying
my afternoon tea, of course.
That's not what I meant.
You haven't been
to class all day.
Is everything all right?
Thanks for the concern,
but I finished
my high school studies ages ago.
There's no need
for me to go to class,
so I'd much rather kill time
by doing this.
You must have good grades
if you're already done.
But still, you won't
make friends by being alone.
It's sweet you're so worried.
Might that be the same reason
why you threw yourself in front
of those girls yesterday?
They're my friends, and it was
the right thing to do.
You don't say. That's one more
thing to admire about you.
[clears throat]
You're not the only one
with questions about yesterday.
So why did you--
Hold that thought
for just a moment.
If you'd like an answer, you'll
have to do something for me.
Now let's think.
Yes, I've got it.
Come with me right away, please.
But, Miss, where are you goi--
Huh?
[LILITH] I won't say it again.
--Uhh...
--[helicopter approaches]
Uh...
[breathes angrily]
So, Mr. Kokone thinks he can
skip my class again, does he?
He's gonna get it!
Why isn't Tor here?
What could he be doing?
Probably something
really perverted, that dog.
Tor.
Tor! Look, it's Turner!
Turner's my favorite!
When you said, "Come with me,"
I never thought it would be
to a theme park!
[LILITH] "Theme park"?
I beg your pardon!
This is the legendary
dark fantasy world
of love and nightmares!
Welcome to Deathlyland!
[BOTH] Uhh...
Uh...
Do you think you could
turn it down a notch, maybe?
How can I? I've been planning
a visit to this park ever since
I decided I'd be coming
to this country to find you!
Oh! Look, it's Rogers!
Wow, it's really him!
You've got to take
a picture of us together!
[laughs]
Well, come on, let's go!
Look, I don't know
about this! Ah!
--[LILITH laughs]
--[breathes shakily]
Whoa, what's the rush?
Hey, come on.
Just wait a second, would ya?
And why would we do that?
Look, Tor!
Deathlyland awaits!
[laughing]
[TOR] I'm gonna get
in so much trouble for this!
[LILITH]
Hurry up! Come on!
[sighs]
[ALL scream]
[LILITH laughs]
[LILITH]
Look, over there! Turner!
[TOR]
Oh, Turner!
You're just so adorable!
I'm so happy I got to meet you!
[WOMAN's voice]
Three, two, one. Now printing.
[TOR sighs]
You know, for an Exceed,
you sure do
get exhausted easily.
In this case, it's way more
mental than physical,
I can assure you of that.
Hey! Let's go in there next!
Come on!
Huh?
[KIDS playing]
[roars]
[laughs]
[shrieks]
[laughs harder]
[yells]
Wow, you're amazing!
Well, I should be!
Ever since I was really little,
my favorite hobbies have been
hunting and shooting.
Whoa, hunting and shooting, huh?
Well, that's pretty uncommon
where I come from.
Really? Back home in England,
doing things like that
isn't rare at all.
I've dismantled and assembled
guns time and again.
You should learn and know
everything you can
about a weapon
that can take a life,
especially if you'd entrust
your own life to it.
As a result of this,
guns are the weapons
I'm most familiar with.
In fact, to be real honest,
it's like they're my soul.
So, they mean that much.
Isn't your Blaze the same way?
Um, I guess so.
--[LILITH] Look out!
--[gasps]
[roars]
--Nicely done!
--Uh...
--[giggles]
You two are
our top scorers today,
and, actually,
you're the highest, ma'am,
so you take home
a special prize!
[giggles] I can't believe
I won a Rogers!
Even better, this chap's
a limited-edition
park exclusive!
Geez, you're acting
just like a little kid!
And what exactly's wrong
with that?
[both chuckle]
--[fireworks popping]
--[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH] Ah.
[LILITH] Since you've fulfilled
your part of the deal,
what was it
you wanted to ask me?
[TOR] Well, why did
you use your Blaze
in front
of all those people yesterday?
[LILITH] Oh, that?
It's only natural
to use your Blaze
in front of your Duo partner.
Huh?
[LILITH] I was so excited
when I learned there was
another wielder
of an Unrivaled Blaze out there.
I felt like I was
the only one, Tor,
but then to hear
I wasn't alone--
that was when I knew it.
That you, the Irregular,
could be the only
Duo partner for me.
I'm the only one? Are you sure?
[gasps]
My Blaze is an offensive weapon,
but yours, it's a defensive one.
You-- you're just like
a guardian knight, Tor.
As you know, I usually tell
people, "I won't say it again,"
But in your case, I will,
so please be my partner.
[music continues]
[no discernible dialog]
Mmm?
--[rattles]
--[grunts]
[sighs] Well, I guess
it is way past curfew.
--[JULIE] Tor. Tor!
--Uh... huh?
[grunts]
Welcome back, Tor.
Hey, thanks for letting me in.
I owe you one.
[BOTH gasp]
[TOR]
The resident advisor.
[grunts]
[sighs]
Uh, ah! Oh, by the way,
I'm sorry that I'm so late.
Nej. It's no problem at all,
but where exactly have you been?
Actually... a theme park.
I went to it with Lilith.
Lilith, huh?
And that's not all.
She also asked me
to be her Duo partner.
But still...
[fireworks exploding]
What?
Look, I'm really sorry,
but I told you
I've already got a Duo partner,
so I can't be yours, Lilith.
[gasps]
But we're more alike!
That may be so,
but I swore to her,
and to myself,
that I'd stand by her always.
[no discernible dialog]
I'm flattered, but my feelings
aren't going to change.
[gasps]
I'll never forgive you for
rejecting my invitation twice,
or myself for asking again.
[sighs]
So, I guess now
she really hates my guts.
And to be honest, she did ask me
to be her partner before,
but I didn't want you to worry.
I should've told you.
I'm really sorry.
Nej. You were doing it
just to protect my feelings,
and I appreciate it.
But more than that...
[gasps]
I'm so thankful, Tor,
that you chose me over her.
No, wait. I'm the one
who needs to be thanking you.
[sneezes]
Let's head back
to our room, okay?
It's pretty chilly out here.
It is, so...
Julie?
...I'll do this to warm up.
It's helping already.
[chuckles]
Yeah. It's nice and toasty.
Ja.
Wherever you went, I hope
you made it back safe, Tor.
[TOMOE] I'm done, so the
bathroom's all yours, Miyabi.
Thanks.
Please be okay, Tor. All right?
Um, Miyabi. Look,
I'm not a prude or anything,
but do you think
maybe you could do that
somewhere a little more private?
Like, oh, I don't know,
in the bathroom?
Huh? [gasps]
Yes, sorry about that.
Guess my head's focused
somewhere else tonight!
[whimpers]
--Uhh...
--[door opens, closes]
This is so unfair!
[RITO] Now that the naughty
student who unwisely decided
to skip class yesterday
has been duly punished,
I have an announcement!
It's time you guys took on
the second-year students
in an interclass battle
in what's called...
The Mordraco!
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--Another battle so soon?
The Mor-what-ha?
[RITO] This time
you won't be fighting
as Duos against other Duos,
but as class against class!
In fact, all the first-year
students will take on
a select group
of second-year ones!
--[weapons clanging]
--[STUDENTS grunting]
[RITO] If you guys think
you've got the upper hand
because there are more of you,
boy, have you got
another think coming!
Those second-year students
are all Level 2,
and some are even Level 3!
In other words,
some of the students
that you'll be fighting
are just as powerful as I am!
[STUDENTS gasp]
So if you don't have a firm
strategy, you guys are gonna get
the ever-living snot
kicked out of you!
Now, good luck
and do your best, okay?
I hope my words
were encouraging!
No, they were anything but that!
And we don't need you to see
that these guys are gonna
give us a run for our money.
Even so, we're not inexperienced
fighters any more.
Ja. And not only that,
but all of us are
much stronger now, as well.
[humphs] I don't care if they
are stronger than us, Tatsu.
I can't wait
to take these bozos on!
[grunts]
Um, am I the only here
who's really scared
about this fight?
Hey, don't worry, Miyabi.
This is gonna be a group effort.
We're all gonna pull together,
rely on each other,
and win this battle
as a unified class.
--[BOY] Who are you?
--[BOTH] Huh?
[STUDENTS gasp]
It's Lilith.
I hate to interrupt,
but might we please
get this Mordraco battle
started right away?
As the first year
student representative,
I'll be taking on
all of you alone.
No one fights
in the Mordraco alone.
You must be pulling
our legs, right?
Quit joking around
and just get off the field.
You don't believe me?
Let me prove it to you.
--[gunshot]
--[grunts]
[STUDENTS gasp]
[TOMOE]
Her Blaze is a rifle!
[gasps]
Well, now that that's sorted,
let's get started, shall we?
--[gunshot]
--[grunts]
Lilith took all of 'em out.
[SAKUYA] My, this is a problem.
I do realize that you're
an Exception, Lilith,
but now you've ruined the chance
for our first year students
to test their strength.
Oh, they'll still get
their chance.
In fact, to allow them
the opportunity,
I've decided to hold
a dance party for everyone.
It will be a very different type
of party, however.
We'll dress up in Blazes,
the music will be
the clash of weapons,
and as host,
I'll dance with everybody.
Hmm.
Wow! So then
you're gonna take on
all these first-year
kiddos alone?
You sure are a feisty
little thing, Miss Priss!
Now as for the theme
of our dance, let's think.
[BOTH gasp]
Yes, that's apropos.
It's "Survive."
Lilith is an Unrivaled,
and she's a crack shot
with that rifle Blaze of hers.
We can't let our guard down.
Ja. You're right.
And we won't lose!
Julie?
Next time, "Survive."
Don't worry,
I've got your back, Tor.