[flames roaring]
--[gunshots]
--[screaming]
[groans]
Hyah!
[grunts]
Imari and Miwa, I need you two
to go take care of the injured!
You got it!
Okay!
Tora and Tatsu, come--
[groans]
Hmm.
There's something different
about these guys now.
[TOMOE thinking]
Please be all right, Miyabi.
I can say with
absolute certainty
that this is Equipment
Smith's team.
These new Units,
they're not the same
as they were last time.
They're Rebels.
The so-called
"god-destroying corps".
It seems that they have
lived up to their name.
[laughing] Well, if you ask me,
the name is super dramatic.
But that doesn't change
the fact that as we speak,
they're giving
our little Level 2's
a pretty serious spanking.
Luckily, there hasn't been
a single casualty reported.
He must not want any.
And in fact, knowing
what I do about him,
this is what that older
gentleman would
call a first-round Selection.
Only a barbarian
could take pride in
something as brutal as this.
Sarah, is the main school
sending reinforcements?
Well, Miss,
about that.
So the campus is being
attacked by another squadron?
Damn.
They want the underground
research facility.
Or so I assume.
I accounted for this
in my plans, as well. Rito?
[laughs]
Well, it's about time!
[SAKUYA] It's not every day
we have a Selection.
Since this is such
a special occasion,
why don't you show them
the true extent of your power?
Hmph!
[laughs]
You don't have to ask
me twice, Headmistress.
It's been too long since I've
had the chance to go all out.
--[gunshots]
--[humming and footsteps]
[laughs]
[grunting]
[screaming]
Hyaaaaaah!
[panting]
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you, Imari.
That's just what partners do.
However, we won't last long.
Hey, Tomoe,
you got any bright ideas?
Only if they come
a little closer.
[screaming]
'Bout time!
Tor!
Hey, guys.
Sorry I'm late.
These jerks have destroyed
nearly everything in their path.
Unforgivable.
[distant cackling]
Why on earth would you
pick a fight with us?
I guess that's the main
question I'd like to ask you.
But first, I should warn you.
I'm not pulling any punches!
[gasps]
Hiyaaah!
I'm not gonna lie,
it feels pretty good
having that stupid
limiter out of the way!
Now who else wants
to see what I can do?
[screaming]
[grunting]
[screaming and grunting]
Come on, come on, come on.
Don't tell me that's all
you weenies have got?
Is she?
Yeah.
She's way stronger
than she was before.
[SQUAD LEADER]
This woman's an exception!
Go ahead and kill her!
I can see that some of
you didn't get enough
in that first go-around.
In that case.
[grunts]
[screaming]
Here's an extra lesson, class.
But keep your distance so you
kids don't get chopped to bits!
This one is Lesson Number Three:
Using your Blaze!
When an Exceed goes
beyond Level Four,
she can release the power
hidden deep in her Blaze.
Just like this!
Now time to devour
them, Ouroboros!
[screaming]
[grunts]
[whimpering]
[screaming]
Take your partner
and dance like mad.
Hand in hand with
the moon rabbit!
What's up, Irregular?
You were going
easy on us before.
[laughs] Yeah, let's just say
it's a grown-up thing.
Now listen.
Tell me what you saw.
Well.
I think I finally got to see how
powerful your Blaze really is.
That's exactly what it was.
Where are you going?
Duh, where else?
This bunny's heading
out on a foxhunt.
Tor?
Let's get back to
the others, 'kay?
Yeah, sure thing.
--[panting]
--[footsteps approaching]
Hey, Tor.
Is Miyabi not here
with you guys?
[gasps]
The main school says
the entire squad that was
attacking them has been--
[groaning]
Absurd.
Everyone's been downed
by a single combatant?
[slicing]
[groans and gurgling]
They managed to wipe
out the attackers!
Well, you've got them right
where you want them, don't you?
I should've known.
[MAN]
I wouldn't be so sure.
We have come here
to collect you.
Blaze Diabolica.
So both the main corps
and the academy attack.
They were just diversions?
Hmph.
They were simply sideshows
to entice the Blaze Diablolica.
Your employer must really have
his heart set on Exceeds, eh?
That's right, now
come with us, or else.
I have to say I'm quite aghast
at your utter lack of manners.
How dare you enter a lady's
room without knocking.
That just won't do.
I'm very sorry.
But unlike last time we met,
I'm afraid that I don't have
an invitation for you today.
Look out, Miss!
[gunshots]
Even if you did, I'd tell
you the same thing.
Don't make me say it again.
Well, That's an
Exception for you.
It's clear that you've
become even stronger
and more beautiful
than you were before.
[cocks gun] But I haven't the
time nor the inclination
to entertain you right now.
Farewell.
[screams]
What the hell?
Was anybody in there?
Well, I think
the headmistress was.
Along with Lilith
and her assistant, too.
You go deal with that.
Before I do anything else, I've
got to find out where Miyabi is.
Did you guys get separated
back on the beach?
She took off a while back.
I'm sorry.
[TOMOE] There's no
need to apologize.
This isn't your fault.
I will find Miyabi
if it's the last thing I do.
I should go with you.
You're going to need someone
who's familiar with the island.
Then let's go.
[panting]
[TOR]
Over there!
Oh, dear me!
Are you okay, Miss?
Lilith! Is everyone all right?
Hello, Tor.
It seems we've been had.
She jumped in the way,
trying to protect us.
My mind was made up.
I simply wasn't going to let
them hurt either one of you.
[grunts]
Whoa, take it easy.
[LILITH]
Don't worry about me.
You have to help her.
Wait, help who?
Sakuya.
I'm ashamed to admit it, but,
I failed and they took her.
Please find her
and bring her back.
Will you promise me
that you'll do that?
Yeah.
You ready, Julie?
Ja.
You can admit it now.
You have nothing left
in your arsenal.
[grunts]
That far of a fall is kinda
pushing it a little bit.
Even so,
we made it.
That's right.
We sure did.
[TOR]
Why did you attack us?
[K] Why I do what
I do is my business.
It's of no concern to you.
[TOR] When you opened fire on my
friends, you made it my concern.
[K] You won't be concerned
with anything if I kill you.
Listen up.
Despite all appearances,
I can assure you
I'm a truly merciful man.
As such, I'll forgive
your interruption
if you jump off this boat
in the next five seconds.
I don't need five seconds.
I told Lilith I'd bring Sakuya
back and I'm a man of my word.
Like Tor, I refuse as well.
And because I can't swim.
[laughs]
I didn't realize
how funny you two are.
Well, enough talk.
Let's get down to it, shall we?
Finally.
I'll eliminate you obstacles.
Julie! Let's go!
Ja.
[grunting]
How do you like this?
Hyah!
[bones crunching]
What a remarkable
power you have.
It's amazing, really,
for just flesh and blood.
[grunts]
[screams]
Oh, whoops!
We can't stop now!
Ja!
[grunting]
Good, but not enough!
Hyaaaaah!
You almost landed that.
Almost.
Yeah?
Well, how about this?
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
Aaaah!
Now, let's find
the headmistress.
[VOICE]
That was quite a blow.
[gasps]
That was a direct hit
that should have killed you.
Sort of.
It might have been fatal
to someone else.
However.
Such an attack has
no effect on me.
So that's the new Unit Equipment
Smith has been developing?
It appears to be quite powerful.
Just as you Exceeds
have surpassed humanity
with the power of your Lukifers,
we have now surpassed
you with the power of Units.
I'm sure you'll agree.
Oh, yeah?
[TOR thinking] Maybe they're
more powerful than my fists.
But what about Julie's sword?
Have we finished
with the chitchat yet?
Excellent.
Because I'd like to
make my move now.
Hyah!
[screaming]
Is that all you've got?
I can barely feel it.
[JULIE]
Hrungnir!
The roar of thunder!
[grunting]
[yelps]
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
So what now?
One more round, all right?
Ja.
[grunts]
[screams]
Tor!
[whimpering]
Breaking through
your special move
was enough to
throw you off, huh?
You have so much to learn.
[grunts]
[yelps]
[whimpers]
And losing your cool just
because your partner's hurt?
The only way I could
describe this behavior
is completely hopeless.
That's why
you will die!
[TOR grunts]
--[K laughs]
--[TOR panting]
You move well
with that injured leg.
I promised her
that I would protect
her no matter what.
Protect her?
Don't make promises
you can't keep!
[groaning and screaming]
[K]
Say that again?
[TOR grunts]
Aaaaaagh!
[K]
What a lovely voice you have.
Now I want you to repeat
to me what you said
about how all you
want is to protect her.
[TOR screaming and groaning]
Tor.
Papa!
Julie.
Don't.
Be a good girl and wait there.
Just be patient and
soon enough I'll
send you to your grave as well.
You won't.
I won't let you.
Sorry, I have to protect Tor.
I swore I always would.
I made that promise to myself.
And I'll keep it!
Hyaaaaaaaaaah!
She's so fast!
These moves.
How is she doing this?
[gasps]
[TOR]
Julie!
[K screaming]
[TOR]
Julie, stop!
It's okay.
That's enough!
Julie!
Julie.
[K]
Incredible.
You've been hiding all
that power this whole time?
[TOR]
You!
Do you actually expect me
to believe that you could
protect this girl considering
the shape you're in?
I do.
Because I'll do
whatever it takes
to keep all my friends safe!
Hearing you spout
nonsense like that,
it makes me sick.
Do you really think you're
good enough to protect her?
How could a broken-down runt
like you protect anybody?
[gasps]
[growls]
[beeping]
Stand by a little longer.
I have in my possession
the Blaze Diabolica, sir.
[MAN]
That won't be necessary.
As luck would have it,
we already have
what we came here for.
But.
[MAN] We must prepare
for another banquet.
I'm ordering you to
return immediately, K.
Understood, sir.
I never did catch your name.
I'm Tor Kokonoe.
Nice to formally meet
you, Tor Kokonoe.
I'll kill you the next
time we cross paths.
I give you my word as a Rebel.
You can call me K.
Wait!
I'm going to remember that name.
You made it!
So Tor was able to
keep his promise, eh?
Yes.
We must find a way to thank him.
Tell me.
Why would your captors
give you up so easily?
The answer to that
is elementary, my dear.
Obviously I was never the older
gentleman's intended target.
Do you mean--
[phone ringing]
Yes, hello?
Fine, go ahead.
[gasps]
It's an invitation
to the Reign Conference.
Isn't it?
[JULIE]
Papa.
He was the hero of Gimle.
One winter night,
Papa went into battle,
and lost.
To him.
Papa was kind
and loving to the very end.
He patted my head and smiled.
As if to say,
"I'm sorry."
And then, the same man
who murdered my father,
he gave me the scar
that runs down my back.
That's why I want to be strong.
Strong enough to kill
that man for what he did.
And strong enough to
avenge the death of my father.
That's the whole reason why I
came to study at Koryo Academy.
That's why you said you're
an avenger like me?
Ja.
But Tor,
even so,
you've still had to
protect me a lot.
I'm so weak.
No, you're not.
You've protected me.
But you're the one who's always
working so hard to protect me.
Well, yeah, of course.
I am your partner after all.
Ja.
That's right,
and I'm your partner.
Mm.
[TOR thinking] All I want
is to keep Julie safe,
so she'll never get
hurt like this again.
And that's why
I've got to get stronger.
Will this thing really
make me stronger?
Yes.
I think you'll find that
it's incredibly effective.
Especially for those who
know their own weaknesses.
I guarantee it.
[gasps]
So what do you say?
Remember this is a
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
A chance for you to grow
stronger in every possible way.
[MIYABI thinking]
If I were stronger,
maybe Tor would...
[TOR] I didn't have
the slightest idea.
Not about why this
Academy was made,
or about what this Academy
was actually making.
None of it.
[JULIE]
Next time: "Reign Conference."
This is reality.
Get used to it.