[grunting]
It's no use. I gotta Blaze!
[TOR]
Julie.
Your fang's
not gonna stop this!
[birds chirping]
[IMARI] Oh, so that's what they
mean by "pretty young thing."
Ah!
Hi! I guess you're
new here, too.
Do you maybe want
to walk together?
[TOR] So this is Koryo
Academy High School.
[IMARI]
I know, can you believe it?
The elite institution founded
by the Dorn Agency
that's all expenses paid.
This place
is a dream come true!
Out of all the kids from my
middle school, I'm the only one
who got accepted here.
Truth be told,
I'm a little nervous.
I guess that makes
two of us then.
So, um,
the martial techniques
that we'll study here.
How rough do you think
the training will be?
Well...
-[metal clanging]
-[screams and grunting]
[IMARI]
Oh.
I haven't even
introduced myself yet.
I'm Imari Nagakura.
It's a pleasure to meet
a fellow new student!
Hello, my name's Tor Kokonoe.
The pleasure's all mine,
Miss Nagakura.
[IMARI]
Please, call me Imari.
[FEMALE PA]
Attention,
the opening ceremony
will begin in ten minutes.
Shall we?
[TOR]
Yeah. Let's go.
[FEMALE PA]
New students, please assemble
in the study hall.
I want to personally welcome
all you new students
to Koryo Academy.
I'm Sakuya Tskumo,
the headmistress
of this institution.
Congratulations on
making it here.
To start things off,
we'll begin by performing
our traditional
Screening Rite.
First, please take note of
the person sitting beside you,
because he or she
will be your partner.
It looks like you and me
are teaming up, Imari.
Yeah, I guess so
but I wonder for what?
[SAKUYA]
When I give the signal,
you're all to rise and
begin battling your partner.
[STUDENTS gasping]
Only the winners
will be permitted entrance.
The losers' Lukifers
will be removed.
And they'll be asked to
leave the premises.
[STUDENTS gasp]
But I got an acceptance letter
to this school!
[MALE STUDENT] Me, too!
Isn't that enough to get us in?
[FEMALE STUDENT]
A battle? Is she serious?
[SAKUYA]
Oh, I should add
that if your battle
isn't over in ten minutes,
both you and your
partner will fail.
[IMARI]
Headmistress!
[SAKUYA]
Yes, you there.
Isn't it a bit extreme
to kick us out just because
we lost a battle?
[SAKUYA] If you can't pass this
special entrance examination,
then you don't belong here.
This test's purpose,
and that of Koryo Academy,
is to teach you how to survive
based on one simple rule.
You must defeat others
to stay alive.
Yeah, but this is
only our first day!
You'll all be plunging headfirst
into battle soon enough
so what better time to
start than right now?
[STUDENTS gasping]
[SAKUYA] You must have
known you'd be engaging
in battles when you first
expressed interest
in attending the Academy.
Excuse me, but can
we switch partners?
[IMARI gasps]
[SAKUYA]
No, and understand this.
The person beside you now
is your first enemy.
[grunts]
[IMARI]
It's okay, Tor.
I appreciate what
you're trying to do.
But still,
I can hold my own.
Now do battle!
You are heaven-chosen
children, the Elcidae!
You've already been given
all the power you require.
Go forth, and use this
soul-power, your Blaze,
prove you're worthy to
enter our hallowed halls!
Blaze on.
Ah!
Bring it!
--[grunting]
--[swords clanging]
[whimpering]
[STUDENTS grunting, yelling]
There's something
I have to do, in fact,
it's the reason
why I came here.
Imari.
And so, I can't
lose to you today!
Blaze on!
--[swords clanging]
--[STUDENTS grunting]
[IMARI]
Tor, unleash your Blaze.
All right.
I gave you a chance!
Ahhhh!
[TOR] So that's the power
of her Lukifer.
My next strike won't miss!
Hyaaaaah!
Aaaaah!
[IMARI panting]
C'mon, that's enough.
Are you telling me
you're giving up?
You can't be serious!
But you barely even fought me!
[IMARI gasps]
[TOR gasps]
Huh?
A shield?
Is that your Blaze, Tor?
That's right.
But, a Blaze,
your soul power...
it's always supposed to
manifest in the form
of a weapon, isn't it?
I guess that means
I'm an Irregular.
All right.
I do appreciate you
protecting me just then.
However,
as I told you, I have
my reasons for being here.
I'm sure that you
have your own as well.
[grunts]
If you don't,
then fall!
She only died because
she was too weak.
[gasps]
I'm real sorry, Imari.
But I've got to be
admitted here!
Oh, yeah, well, so do I!
[BOTH grunting]
Ah!
[IMARI gasps]
Again, I'm sorry.
Mmmm!
Yah!
[IMARI yelps]
Time's up, people.
As I mentioned, only the victors
will be permitted entry.
Need help?
[SAKUYA] I will now leave you
with these parting words.
You victors,
congratulations.
May you all someday
reach Absolute Duo.
All that fancy fighting
and no one got hurt.
I've gotta admit,
I'm a little surprised.
Well, you know, since Blazes are
weapons produced by your soul,
I suppose souls are the
only things they can hurt,
so that would leave
the body untouched.
So is that why you were
holding back in there?
I didn't use the full
power of my Blaze
because I was afraid
that I might hurt you, Imari.
That was very sweet of you.
However, you can't
do that anymore.
[IMARI] It doesn't matter
what your power is, or how
strong or weak your
opponent may be.
If you lose once,
then that's it.
That's the kind of world that's
out there waiting for us.
And once you lose,
there are no do-overs.
Congrats on making it in, Tor.
Take care now. Buh-bye.
[grunts]
[MAN]
What's it been, two years?
Huh?
You know, Tor, I never thought
we'd meet again here
of all places.
Tora? It is you!
[TORA]
Hmm. So you made it through the
Screening Rite, too, huh?
I guess that makes
you and me both
two more guinea pigs for
Sakuya Tsukumo, doesn't it?
Wow, that's a real negative
way of looking at things.
C'mon, think about it, man.
We got our Blaze powers
from those Lukifer things
she gave us.
There's gotta be an ulterior
motive for giving us those,
don't you think?
If you ask me, this whole
school is nothing but a big
research lab for Sakuya,
and we're just lab rats
in her experiment.
Oh, hey, look, there's the
first-year classroom, Tora.
We should probably
get a move on.
Hmm. Hey, what's
the big hurry, "lab rat"?
You think you're
ready for this?
Yeah, I sure am!
[door clacks]
[bells jingling]
[STUDENTS whispering]
[FEMALE STUDENT]
She's so cute!
Whoa, it's her.
Do you know that girl?
Well, I've seen
her before but...
You're Tor.
Uh...
Hey, do I know her?
How am I supposed to
answer that question?
[TORA]
Dude, she's looking at you.
Yeah, I can see that,
but I don't know why.
[TORA]
Why don't you ask her?
Yeah, all right,
I think I can do that.
Hey, so I uh--
Um, I...
So, tell me--
Ugh.
[TORA]
Wow. She's good.
[TOR groans]
[WOMAN]
Hello, hello!
Nice to meet you,
I'm your homeroom teacher
Rito Tsukimi, but I insist you
call me "Professor Bunbun."
What's with
the strange looks, class?
Oh! I get it, you're all dazzled
by how gosh-darn cute I am.
Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh?
[STUDENTS] No, we just
didn't expect a teacher
who'd be wearing bunny ears.
[TOR] All this and
she's still looking at me?
Well, since I've
introduced myself to you,
now it's your turn, class!
Tomoe Tachibana.
Um, my name is Miyabi Hotaka.
Aoi Torasaki.
[grunts]
[RITO] 'Kay, and next is
you there in the back.
I'm Tor Kokonoe.
Kokonoe?
Oh, right! So you're
that Irregular, huh?
You were the talk
of the teacher's lounge!
Oh, I was?
[RITO] Now you, the
silver-haired girl beside him,
please stand up!
Yeah, my name's Julie Sigtuna.
And I'm pleased to meet
each and every one of you.
[TOR thinking]
Julie, huh?
What is this girl's deal?
[RITO] To make sure you've
gotten the hang of this place,
let's review some things.
Remember, your student ID can
also be used as a credit card.
Plus you get
100,000 yen each month
to use how you like!
Boys, if you don't know what
to spend all that dough on,
I accept tips! Tee-hee!
[BOTH groaning]
Now let's talk about the special
Duo system we have here.
You'll be paired up
with a partner
and you guys will
do everything together
from training to eating
to sharing a room.
[JULIE]
Hmm.
[TOMOE]
Professor?
Yes, dear?
Can you tell us why the
Academy has such a system?
Well, the answer to that
is once you graduate,
all of you will be placed
in the Dorn Agency's
peacekeeping corps.
And when you're there, you'll
be working in teams.
Primarily in teams of two!
So then I guess we're
getting used to what
life in the corps will be like.
Is that correct?
Bingo, you hit the nail
right on the head!
[TOMOE]
Thank you. You're too kind.
Two Duo partners
work together as one
everywhere they go,
whether it's in the classroom
or in the dorms,
and speaking of which,
all partners will also be
doubling up as roommates!
All right, now listen up!
Permanent Duos will
be discussed and decided
officially by this
weekend, okay?
So until then, all of you will
be placed in temporary Duos!
[TOR]
Temporary, huh?
Well, Tora what do you say?
Yes, I suppose we could
work something out.
[RITO]
While these Duos are temporary,
they are pre-assigned.
And by "pre-assigned"
I mean that
the person next to
you will be your partner
like in the screening rite.
The person...
Next to me's...
[TOR]
My partner?
[JULIE]
Mm.
We can change that, right?
Sorry, already been decided!
No, please, you've
gotta be kidding me!
Consider yourself lucky!
You get an exotic,
beautiful girl
as a partner and roommate!
That reminds me, Koryo Academy
is no place for infants.
So no funny business.
Oh, man, this sucks!
[STUDENTS]
Are you serious?
This is my roommate?
Really?
Please, Professor Bunbun,
I'm begging you,
this isn't sensible!
Remember this morning's
opening ceremony?
This school made you students
savagely fight each other
and was that sensible?
Ah!
[TORA]
Just be a man and suck it up!
[TOR] That's the problem!
I am a man!
[TORA] Boo-hoo,
it's time for lights out!
No, wait!
[sighs]
[groans]
Geez, what should I say
when I walk in there?
Good evening!
Excuse me, miss.
Guten Abend!
Now wait a minute.
This is my room,
too, so I can just
walk in and not
say anything at all.
Here goes.
Um, it's me, Tor.
She's not here.
Maybe she wasn't too thrilled to
have me for a roommate, either,
and crashed someplace else.
[TOR]
Hmm?
[gasps]
I'm sorry.
I hope you don't mind
that I showered first.
Ah, wait, what the hell
are you wearing?
My pajamas.
Oh, no, no, no, those
are definitely not pajamas!
If I sleep in it,
that makes it pajamas.
What else would it be?
[screaming]
[clears throat]
Um. Why don't I just
reintroduce myself, okay?
Hi, I'm--
Tor, right?
[TOR]
Oh, so you remembered.
Your name's hard to forget.
It sounds a lot like the word
"Thor" that's used
in my homeland, Gimle.
Gimle, huh?
And where exactly
in the world is that?
Scandinavia.
And Thor, of course, is
a thunder god and one of the
mightiest in all of
Norse mythology.
[JULIE]
It's a good name.
So cool, that's one of
the mightiest gods.
Hey, Tor?
Is something wrong?
Um, no, it's just that--
Well, to be honest, I noticed
you were staring at me
all through class today,
kinda like you are now.
Do you mind explaining
to me why?
It's because I'm
interested in you, Tor.
Huh?
You heard me.
Really interested, in fact.
You're the only thing
I've thought about.
So by "interested,"
do you mean--?
Huh? Wait, hold on!
Aren't you taking
this a little too fast?
We just met this morning!
[gasps]
I saw you use this exact move
back at the Screening Rite.
And it's interested me
ever since.
Oh. So...
--The move, huh?
--Yeah, Tor.
Do you think you could
teach it to me?
Um. I'm sorry.
But I can't 'cause it puts way
too much strain on the body.
If a girl your size tried it,
it might destroy her.
So, I'm sorry, but I can't.
Are you sure, Tor?
That's too bad.
[TOR]
Hmm?
Are you okay?
My apologies.
It must be
the time difference.
I'm so tired,
I could fall asleep.
No problem. I'm sorry
I acted so spazzy tonight.
Now go get some sleep,
Miss Sigtuna.
Ja, Tor.
I think I will go do that.
So good night,
and sweet dreams.
Hey, wait! I didn't
mean on the floor!
Where's your bed at? You're
gonna catch a cold out here!
[breathing softly]
Ahhh!
Crap!
[TOR grunts]
And it's still only
the first day.
I better turn in as well.
[liquid pouring]
As if I could even sleep!
[sighs]
[JULIE]
What was that you just said?
[groans sleepily]
[TOR]
I'm sorry, did I wake you?
Oh, nej.
What is that?
It's just some instant
apple tea I made.
That's all.
It smells so good.
Yeah, it does.
Do you want some?
Ja.
Well, here you go.
Thank you very much, Tor.
Ah!
Delicious.
Hey, I've been
thinking, Miss Sigtuna.
Nej, Tor.
"Julie" is fine, okay?
Oh, all right then.
Anyway, I'd like to
make this work
till the real duos
are announced.
--That okay, Julie?
--Ja, Tor.
I'd very much like to
make this work as well,
my new "partner."
[TOR] What exactly
does "Ja" mean anyway?
[JULIE] It means "yes."
It's always "yes."
[TOR]
Ja!
[JULIE]
Ja, "ja."
[TOR]
Ja?
[JULIE]
Ja, "ja."
[TOR]
Ja?
[JULIE]
Next time, "Duo."
[TOR]
Ja. That's deep.