[birds chirping]
[exhales]
[WOMAN] Sarah. Tell me,
is everything ready?
[SARAH]
Just as you asked, Miss.
Thank you.
Guess it's time, then,
to go meet my kindred.
They're the same
as you are, Miss?
Is that correct?
The same, yet different.
To be precise,
only one of us is an exception.
Don't you see
that I'm just like you?
I'm an Avenger.
[gasps]
What the--?
Was I dreaming?
Maybe, but that really happened.
So then, we're both Avengers.
What is this?
Mm?
Julie, what the heck?
Ahh!
Oh. Wow, it's so soft!
No, must stop!
What, Tor?
Julie! I'm so sorry!
For what?
Wait, hold on!
I know this looks bad,
but I can explain everything--
[screams]
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect you
to be sleeping next to me,
and when I moved my hand,
I got a "handful."
Sorry.
So in other words,
if you hadn't done that,
you wouldn't have even
known they were there?
No, that's not it!
Of course I would've known!
It's just that I don't have
much experience,
and all of the sudden,
I move my hand one morning
and it ends up on a girl's boob!
Which I've gotta
admit it was really soft!
Oh, crap! What am I saying?
No, this was all my fault.
Remembering the past
yesterday made me real lonely,
so I crawled into bed with you.
I'm sorry.
Julie.
I'm the one in the wrong
here even if it was an accident.
I'm sorry.
[alarm clock chirping]
Oh!
That reminds me
to tell you something.
I want to wish you
a good morning, Tor.
Aw, thanks. Likewise.
Partner.
Oh! Morning!
[MIYABI]
Yes, good morning, Tor.
You, too, Julie.
[STUDENTS chattering]
What?
Are you guys are well enough
to be back in class already?
[grunts]
Of course we are.
We couldn't let
a few minor injuries
keep us bedridden forever.
They weren't minor,
they were serious.
She did a lot of
damage to the two of you.
I know Lukifers increase
your body's curative power,
but it's still best
not to overdo things.
You said "she."
You mean you know
about Professor Bunbun?
Yeah.
[TOR]
When we didn't all make it back,
Tomoe and Miyabi got worried,
so they came to check on us.
They found you and
provided first aid.
Oh, really?
Tomoe, Miyabi,
thank you.
Huh?
What's the matter, Tor?
Is something wrong?
It's Tora.
He actually bowed to someone?
Hey, what do you think
I am, some kinda ingrate?
[MIYABI whimpers]
Oh!
I'm sorry!
It's fine. Just because
his name means tiger,
doesn't mean that he bites.
Geez, what kind of weird picture
of me do you have in your head?
[giggles]
Hey.
Tell me something, you guys.
Why do you think Miss Tsukimi
went all psycho like that?
[JULIE] She said it was
"all in a day's work," So...
I'd be lying if I
said I wasn't curious.
But luckily, I doubt
we'll have to see her again.
[door opening]
[RITO]
Good morning!
You're all well-rested
after the Novgladius, right?
Well, we've got lots to cover,
so let's get cracking!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[TOR]
Wait!
Oh, dear!
I hope there's not a problem
because I've got
another class to teach.
[laughing]
Are you kiddos
looking for a fight?
It's only morning and
I'm already getting fired up!
You witch.
What the hell are
you doing here?
Now, now, Mr. Kokonoe!
You should show more respect
when addressing
your teachers, okay?
That's a lot to ask
from somebody
who you just tried to kill!
[evil laughter]
True enough!
But since we're
on the topic of respect,
aren't you going
to at least acknowledge
the presence of
our headmistress?
[STUDENTS gasp]
[thud]
[TORA]
What's the meaning of this?
After careful consideration,
I have decided to rehire
Miss Tsukimi.
Are there any other questions?
Are you insane?
In case you forgot, this
nut-job tried to kill us!
That may be true, but all
of you are still alive, yes?
And even after having taken on
someone as strong as her.
I've re-assessed her
skill as an educator,
and no one else on staff can
bring our students to that level
in such a short time.
Ooh!
Hear that, kids? It looks
like you're stuck with me!
With all due respect, ma'am,
haven't you decided
that in hindsight?
Her teaching style is leading
to the outcome
we're striving for here.
Miss Tsukimi may very
well employ unorthodox
teaching methods that can
and will endanger your lives.
But if that is what's
required to inspire all of you
to reach Absolute Duo,
I say so be it.
And also,
in the next few days,
we will hold a Level 2
Rite of Sublimation
for the six of you
assembled here.
Huh. Trying to shut
us up, are you?
It's what you're entitled to
for excelling in the Novgladius,
so, good luck. You're
certainly going to need it.
If you recall,
several times I've told you
that Lukifers have levels.
Today we're going to go over
some very important details--
[TOR thinking] "If that's what
it requires, so be it," huh?
[RITO]... pay attention
and get those pencils ready?
Well, class.
As I'm sure you know,
each level you gain
multiplies your
powers by two or more.
One more level is one thing.
But if you're two levels higher
than your opponent,
it's hopeless!
So you better be careful
who you pick fights with!
[STUDENTS whispering]
[WOMAN] Ah, so you're the
famous Irregular, I take it?
Hmm?
[gasps]
Yes, I am.
My name's Tor Kokonoe.
Okay.
Then come with me. [giggles]
But I'm in the middle
of class here.
Don't make me say it again.
I have special permission to do
what I want, right?
Miss Tsukimi?
Go ahead.
[TOR gasps]
Whatever you need Tor for,
you can do it right here.
This matter doesn't
concern you at all.
Besides, I'd like to speak
to him privately, peon.
[TORA grumbles]
All right then.
Tor?
I'll be right back.
You'll let me borrow your
notes later tonight, won't you?
Oh!
I almost forgot.
I just transferred here
from the England campus.
It's a pleasure
to meet you all.
Right, now my name's
Miss Bristol.
However, you may call me
by my first name, Lilith.
[birds chirping]
Oh, thanks so much.
Uh...
This is good!
Yes.
Your tea is outstanding
as always, Sarah.
Why thank you,
Miss, I'm flattered.
[TOR thinking]
I wish Julie could try this.
[LILITH]
Now, then.
Huh?
Tor Kokonoe.
Starting today, you
shall be my Duo partner.
Wait.
What did you just say?
Don't make me say it again.
Look, I really appreciate
the offer, Lilith, but I can't.
Because I already
have a Duo partner.
I know that.
But it doesn't matter.
The reason is
because I'm special.
I am an Exception, you see.
You're an Exception?
And what is that?
Back in England, I heard
rumors about the Irregular.
So I specifically transferred
here to meet you.
You should be grateful.
You think a lot of
yourself, don't you?
Wait!
Did you just say you
came all the way here
because you wanted to meet me?
Yes. Precisely.
You're unique just like I am,
and another
Unrivaled to be exact.
Therefore,
both you and I are
perfectly suited to be
Duo partners.
Let me stop you there.
Maybe you're unaware of it,
but school rules forbid
breaking up a Duo.
Yes, so what?
The rules at this school
don't apply to me at all.
I'm allowed to do
whatever I want.
I am an Exception.
Well, Mr. Kokonoe,
what do you say?
Not that you need to think
it over, of course.
You're right.
I don't need to.
Then it's settled.
Sure is.
Sorry, but I'm not
partnering up with you.
Or breaking up my current Duo.
[gasps]
Thanks for the tea.
It was delicious.
Now, Tor, wait a minute!
You're actually turning me down?
To borrow a phrase from you,
don't make me say it again.
You have my answer.
Just ten more laps
and you're done!
Are you crazy?
Each lap's four kilometers!
That's an entire marathon,
you monster!
I'm no monster, I'm a bunny!
[laughs]
I can't do anything
about Miss Priss,
but I sure as hell
can punish you
for ducking out of class today!
[growling]
That's so unfair!
Dammit.
She is one nasty vorpal bunny.
[JULIE]
Tor?
Uh, what's up, Julie?
You forgot your towel.
Oh, I did?
Thanks.
Just leave it there
and I'll get it.
Yeah.
Um, I really can't do that
if you're still standing
there watching.
Oh, right.
[door closing]
You're having some, right?
Yeah.
Thank you, Tor.
Huh?
It's delicious once again.
Why, thank you.
Tor, I was wondering.
Mm?
If you don't mind, could
we sleep together tonight?
Hey, come on, now.
That was supposed to be
a one-time thing, remember?
[whimpers]
[TOR thinking]
Oh, no! Not good!
You okay?
Oh, know what
I've been thinking?
That maybe we should go
somewhere on our next break.
Does that sound good?
I mean, we never even left
the school campus, have we?
I think we could use a change
of pace around here, right?
Well?
Yeah, Tor.
I agree with you.
All right, so where
should we go then?
Do you have any suggestions?
To be honest, I would like to
buy some new things to wear.
All I that brought to school
with me were winter clothes.
Okay.
Shopping, huh?
Mm-hmm.
[TOR thinking]
Yes!
I distracted her!
[JULIE]
Tor?
Come on.
Let's get to bed, 'kay?
Yeah.
Look, there's a flock
of seagulls out there.
I also see a big city up ahead.
Yeah, that's where the mall is
where we're gonna go shopping.
Well, if you ask me, the best
place to shop for clothes
is the A La Mode mall.
Cool, thanks a lot, Miyabi.
Oh, hey, if you're free, would
you like to come along with us?
What?
I'm sorry, but I don't
know if I'm emotionally
ready for something like that!
All we're doing is
buying clothes for Julie,
and I thought
it might help her
if she had another
girl's opinion.
Clothes. For Julie?
Oh.
Uh...
I'd love to, but I've already
got plans with Tomoe that day!
Sorry!
No problem.
Maybe next time then, okay?
Uh.
Sure! [giggles]
I know about
the best places in town
thanks to all the helpful
advice Miyabi gave me.
Yeah.
She's a very kind
person, isn't she?
This place is so big.
It is, so don't get lost.
What the--?
Help me, Tor!
Please!
Hold on, Julie!
[BOTH panting]
I'm sorry for getting
into that jam.
No, I'm sorry for not
keeping you close to me.
Oh!
Sorry!
Wait a sec, what are
you doing that for?
So we don't separated.
'Kay?
Yeah, sure.
Awww!
[GIRL 1]
Isn't she gorgeous?
[GIRL 2] Uh-huh, she
looks just like a doll!
We already have gawkers.
Ooh!
Tor, why don't we try
that store over there?
[TOR]
That one?
Sure. Sounds good to me.
Yeah.
Let me just try this dress on
and then I'll be right out.
That girlfriend of
yours is so adorable!
Oh, no, she's not--
You are one lucky guy,
you know that?
Thank you, but--
So are the two of you on a date?
Huh?
Julie!
Oh, wow!
Well, what do you think?
[TOR]
It looks really great on you.
Thank you very much, Tor.
Miss, I'll take this one.
Whoa, that was fast!
You want to try anything else on
while we're here maybe?
That's a great idea!
I'm sure you'll love
these designs.
Yeah. Let's see them then.
[TOR]
That's a good one, really nice.
[JULIE]
I'll take it.
[TOR]
Mmm, cute!
[JULIE] Then I'll be
taking this one, too.
[TOR] Uh, nice and cool,
and for the spring.
[JULIE]
I'll take it as well.
[CLERK] And this one?
What about this one?
Just try it on,
that's all I ask.
You don't even have to buy it!
What, since when?
[JULIE]
May I pay with this?
But of course, this
establishment gladly accepts
Koryo Academy student cards!
[beeping]
I guess you kind of
overdid it, didn't you?
Nej.
These are all lovely
clothes that I really like.
And you said you did, too.
Uh.
Well, your clothes will
be sent to the school.
But since we're here, why
don't we check out the mall?
Yeah.
Let's do that.
[TOR]
Here you go.
I think you said you
wanted strawberry?
Is something the matter, Julie?
No, it's nothing.
Thank you for getting us this.
Sure thing.
Let's dig in, shall we?
This gelato, Miyabi
says it's the best.
If she recommended it,
then I'm sure that it is.
It's really tasty.
I know, right? Mine too!
What did you get?
This is rum raisin.
Do you want to try some?
Yeah, I do.
Ahhh.
You're kidding!
Look, I can't, not in public!
But Papa and Mama used
to always do that for me.
Uh...
Ahhhhh.
[grunting]
[sighs]
All right.
Say "ah."
Ahhhh.
It's so delicious.
I know.
Want more?
No, thank you, but now
I want you to try mine.
Huh?
Tor.
Say "Ah."
Uh, no, thank you. I'm good!
Ahhhhhhh.
[TOR]
Can we be done with this now?
[JULIE]
Nja.
"Nja"?
Why do you look so woozy?
Uh-oh.
Crap! Could the rum raisin
have done this?
Um, hey, Julie.
Are you maybe
feeling a little drunk?
No, Nej.
[slurred]
I am not drunk at all.
Dammit, you're definitely drunk!
Nja, yam not drunk.
How many fingers
am I holding up?
I can see free of you, Tor.
How is this happening?
You gotta get sober!
Let's go get you
some coffee, okay?
Oh, no, Tomoe!
What do you think it means
if he's touching
her face like that?
Geez, calm down, would ya?
Now let's think about this.
Are you positive those two
aren't on an actual date?
If it was an actual date,
why would they invite me along?
But still.
Yeah, good point.
Because there's still suspicion
of illicit activity going on,
we should keep an eye on them.
Besides, look what
he's doing now.
[MEN snickering]
Aw, you two sweet
things look lonely.
You won't be if you
come hang out with us!
[MIYABI whimpers]
No, thank you.
Let's go, Miyabi.
Come on,
just for a little while!
We won't do anything weird!
You dog!
Ow!
Hey, if you're gonna
go hurtin' my buddy,
that means you're definitely
coming along with us!
[TOMOE] He started it
and the answer is no!
You got a lot of nerve
dissing my bro like that!
Just get behind me, Miyabi.
Tomoe.
[MEN laughing]
Hey, you creeps!
You guys better back off!
[MAN]
Says who? You?
Tor, thank goodness.
You're here too, Julie?
Nja.
[BOTH]
Uh?
If you've got a
problem with them
you've got a problem with me
do you understand?
Oh, you're gonna have a problem
once we get done
pounding on you, pal!
[gunshot]
[TOR]
Lilith?
What does she have?
[CROWD]
Wait, were those gunshots?
Those guys are hurt.
Hmm!
An Exception with...
a rifle Blaze?
Oh, man.
That's nuts.
Uh... uh...
You know, Julie.
It's such a coincidence
that you're shopping
for underwear on the
same day as me and Miyabi.
So then, what do
you think about that bra?
How does it fit?
It seems to be a little
too big here in the front.
In that case, you
should get the one
that's sized
a little smaller. Okay?
Yeah.
I'll go do that right away.
[gasping]
[MIYABI]
Oh, Tor, how could you?
[TOMOE]
You're a perv and a dog!
This is so unfair!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Lilith Bristol.
[RITO]
Do it cuter!
Hi, I'm Lilith!
[MIYABI]
Um, what's that girl doing?
[TOMOE]
Good question.
[JULIE]
Next time: "Level Up."
[RITO]
Now kick it up a notch!
Lilith here!
Just what are you making me do?