Miyabi.
I wonder what could
have happened to her.
Let's go look for her
one more time. Okay?
Uh, yeah.
I need your attention, class!
Hello!
Our super-fun seaside
camp has come to an end,
so now we're heading back!
No, I'm not leaving!
Not until I've found Miyabi!
Oh, my, how rebellious!
Defying the orders
of your teacher
and the headmistress as well?
Even if we allowed
you to stay behind,
you couldn't do much!
Wait, but you can't just--
I can and will, so shut it.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Of course,
There's not much I could
do, either, silly me!
[laughs]
[sighs] Dammit!
Oh, Tor.
Hyah!
[BOTH grunting]
We'll take over the search
from here, 'kay, Tor?
And don't worry.
We'll find Miyabi.
[TOR thinking]
That was days ago.
And still no word about
Miyabi being found yet.
[TOR grunting]
You've gotta
concentrate harder, Tor!
[groaning]
Well, go figure.
It seems Tor's more upset
about Miyabi being missing
than even Tomoe is.
Tomoe's strong. Very strong.
[TOR grunting]
[TOR thinking]
Tomoe!
Ahh!
Didn't you hear me?
Concentrate!
[whimpers]
[laughs]
I don't think he can.
Not with your bodacious
boob in his face!
Eh? Ah.
[TOR breathing heavily]
[TOR thinking] Why is it
whenever we spar,
we always end up
in embarrassing positions?
Let's try this again.
I hope you're
ready. Are you?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Haaaaaaaaaaah!
[water running]
Oh, not again!
I forgot my towel.
Mind if I borrow one, Miyabi?
[gasps]
[sighs]
[panting]
Aw, thank you so much, Tomoe!
[cries softly]
[crying continues]
[KIBITSU] Have you
heard anything about
when Miyabi will get
out of the hospital?
[FEMALE STUDENT] No,
but I feel really bad for her,
getting hurt at
summer camp and all.
I hope the poor
thing gets better soon.
[FEMALE STUDENT]
Me, too.
[RITO thinking] Not a word about
Miyabi disappearing to anyone.
It'll just wind up
upsetting the other students.
Uh--
[LILITH]
Guess who?
[gasps]
Good morning, Lilith.
[laughs] Correct!
It's so nice that my future
husband knows me so well!
To be honest,
your accent gave you away.
Oh, drat!
Well, I don't mind.
At least you recognize my voice!
I love that.
You don't seem to
be doing too bad.
Huh?
Uh--
It's you, Julie.
Ja, correct, Tor.
Since you're my partner,
the ties that bind
us both together,
they're stronger
than anyone else's.
Well, perhaps. But that
still remains to be seen.
Ah, Tomoe!
Guess who?
[gasps]
Now wait just a minute, Lilith,
what on earth are you doing?
It's only a comparison
test between us girls!
Oh, what do you know,
they're not half bad at all!
"Not half bad"?
What is that supposed to mean?
[whimpers]
I wonder if Lilith's
weird behavior
is her way of trying
to cheer us up.
Hmm?
Please don't talk about my
boobs in class like that!
Why? It's not like they're
going to get any smaller.
They might even get as
big as mine one day--
Um, Julie?
Oh, really?
Well, I'll show you then!
Just watch, they'll
get even bigger!
[waves crashing]
[MIYABI]
But, Tor.
Why not?
I'm sorry.
But I'm afraid I just
can't do that, Miyabi.
Because.
I think I know.
It's because you're
too weak, isn't it?
Huh?
[blade cutting]
[gasps]
How humiliating.
Tor Kokonoe.
You just can't seem to protect
anyone at all, can you?
Big brother.
[gasps]
That's another one dead, Tor.
It's because you're too weak.
I wonder how it could
have turned out.
If only you had the same
amount of power that I do.
[gasps]
Hey, Tor.
It was the same
nightmare again, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
Geez, how annoying. I'm sorry
for waking you up this late.
Julie?
No, please just let me do this.
This is the same thing that
Mama would always do for me
when bad dreams about
Papa kept me from sleeping.
Thank you so much, Julie.
[SAKUYA] I summoned
you here for one reason.
As a token of my
gratitude for your actions,
I would like to repay you for
rescuing me from the Rebels.
Thanks, but that's
not necessary.
[gasps]
Tor Kokonoe.
I give my permission
for you to undergo
the Level 4 Rite of Sublimation.
I was only one half
of the rescue team.
Julie was the other half.
It took the both of us
together to pull it off.
So then why am I
the only one who's here?
Hmm.
Because you are unique, Tor.
An Unrivaled to be exact.
But why level up me,
and not do it for Julie?
Just what is there
to hesitate about?
You, of all people, want
more power, don't you?
Isn't that why you came to
the Academy in the first place?
With power, you could have
been able to avert a tragedy.
Wouldn't that have been nice?
[TOR thinking]
I'd love to be stronger.
But still.
[sighs]
[gasps]
Look, I'm sorry,
but I don't think I can do this.
Then let's do this, Tor.
Take it and give it
a little more thought.
However, keep in mind
the world waits for no one.
Nor is it so kind to let
you have your way.
Not since it's grown
so dark and full of malice.
You'll know soon enough
since the Academy is
about to host
the Reign Conference.
What is the Reign Conference?
Equipment Smith,
the Master Armorer.
He's the older gentleman
who created the Rebels,
and he'll be there.
[gasps]
[door latches]
Hello Tor, welcome home.
I'll get some apple tea
ready for you, okay?
Uh.
What's wrong?
[birds chirping]
[RITO]
Well, well, Look who's here.
If it isn't the pride
of the Dorn Agency.
The elite security
force Ethnarchs.
A-ha!
They think they're so special
just because they've graduated
and get to wear
those fancy uniforms!
[KIBITSU] We've been forbidden
from leaving school grounds.
I'm not exactly sure
what's going on here,
but I bet it's something big.
[TATSU grunts]
[fountain flowing]
So now they've
pushed Level 3 students
into serving as security.
Sakuya sure knows how
to use people all right.
Well, actually, that just
goes to show you
how important this meeting is.
Besides,
you could do a lot worse
as far as getting
real-life practice goes.
So stay on your guard, okay?
[MAN]
Just leave everything to us.
Appreciate the help,
but we're on top of things.
Right, so if anything
happens today,
you just let us
handle it. Got it?
Yes, sir.
We will. And thanks so much.
[chuckles]
Still.
Ideally, nothing will
happen, of course.
Locked down tight.
I suppose Reign really
is quite the big deal.
It's an invitation to
the Reign Conference.
Isn't it?
Sakuya! How did you know?
[TOR] Lilith!
That's odd.
It's not like you to
leave your post.
Not that I mind.
There's something
I want to know.
You might be able to tell me.
Oh, dear.
If you want to know
how I feel about you,
well, I told you that ages ago.
No, it's about Equipment Smith
and the Reign Conference
on campus.
Just what the hell is
going on around here?
That's what I want to know.
I don't know who told you
I knew, but listen up,
because I won't say it again.
Mmph.
[LILITH]
Equipment Smith.
A key member of
a certain nation's
shadowy military organization.
He's also known in some
circles as the "Master Armorer,"
and he put together the
so-called "god-slaying corps,"
the Rebels.
But for what purpose?
To reach the ultimate
goal that he has,
which is Absolute Duo.
Are you serious?
Just like--
You victors. Congratulations.
May you all someday
reach Absolute Duo.
People brought together with
Absolute Duo at their core.
That's Reign.
And now, its members
are all gathered here.
Hey, I hope you didn't mind if
I poured myself a little drink,
Miss Blaze Diabolica.
I wish I had more to offer.
And please make
yourself at home.
Mister Grave Phantom.
Enchanté.
Pleasure to make your
acquaintance, Diabolica.
Ah, yes, Tempest Judge, is it?
Thank you for coming
and for the rose.
It looks as if you
and Judge are still
like oil and water, aren't you?
Eh, Darkray Disaster?
Like you have to ask.
What a lovely academy you have.
I so envy you.
I would be very proud
if my country had
a school like this.
Thank you so much,
Silent Diva.
[door opens]
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
Shall we start?
[TOR]
Absolute Duo.
What is it, exactly?
The best way I can describe
it is the final frontier.
Your soul-power's extremes.
Why don't we just
leave it at that?
The final frontier you say?
So then by soul power,
do you mean the extremes
of our Blaze weapons?
That's the reason, isn't it?
Why we're all gathered here?
Yes, you see, Koryo Academy
was founded for one purpose
and one alone.
To use the Lukifers
inside us to awaken
the power within our souls,
then that, in turn,
would create Exceeds
all in an attempt to help
us reach Absolute Duo.
Sakuya's path leads there.
That's what she told me.
[LILITH thinking]
Yes, it does,
but she's trying to
reach it all on her own.
Contrary to everyone else.
And rejecting their help.
An alliance?
Exactly.
It is enticing, eh?
Gotta admit,
didn't see one that coming.
Oui, très bien!
I, too, am surprised.
To think a member of Reign
would want to team up!
I'm assuming that all of you
know how powerful my Units are.
Imagine what would
happen if they
joined forces with your Exceeds.
Together we would
control a formidable
army to be reckoned with.
So what do you say,
Miss Sakuya?
My answer is no.
Mm?
[chuckles]
That which I seek and that
which you seek, Mr. Smith,
they both lie down two separate
paths that will never cross.
Their outcomes would
differ as well, naturally.
If I were to join
forces with you,
it would be nothing
but sheer folly.
You stress soul-power here.
Right?
What passes for training at this
academy is very antiquated.
It's nothing but the impurity
of the everyday, in fact.
Dear me, that method is far
too dull for this old fellow.
I doubt in your case
that you'll ever be able
to understand it at all.
I'm like my grandfather.
You not only lost to him once,
but you were also cut
out of his organization.
That is how things occurred.
Unless perhaps
I'm somehow mistaken?
It appears you still
wish to fulfill your ambitions
of days gone by.
Count me out since I have
no interest in the desires
of a pitiful old man.
[MASTER ARMORER laughs]
That's quite harsh!
It's been said your words are
steeped in poison, witch,
but I didn't know
they'd be so toxic.
And,
I won't stand for such rudeness,
or take petty insults such
as yours lightly, so.
How about we settle this?
I suggest we do so
with a little game,
Miss Sakuya.
A game?
What kind?
One that's easy as pie.
The rules are very simple.
My Rebels will attack
this academy.
And in response, your
Exceeds will try to stop them.
And then, whoever wipes out
the other side first wins.
Why don't we call it
a killing game, yes?
I accept. Let's play.
Then it's decided.
[laughs]
Tor, um.
Absolute Duo.
To be honest with you,
I'm still not entirely certain
I understand
what it's all about.
But so many people, they end up
getting hurt in its pursuit.
[TOR thinking] It's true that I
did come to the Academy seeking
to get stronger.
But now,
I wonder,
if I should.
Huh?
I guess,
it's like gaining one thing
while losing another.
But this is reality.
Get used to it.
Doesn't make it any less sad.
[TOR]
You and Sakuya may be right.
What?
What you've said.
I've actually been thinking
that you two may be right.
But I just
didn't want to admit it.
You silly man.
No, of course you wouldn't.
[jet engines approaching]
[ALL gasp]
[ETHNARCH]
Wait, what?
A Rebel attack?
An attack?
It's happening in 10 minutes?
With all due respect, how do
you even know this, sir?
Did you say a killing game?
Oh no, they're here!
Now it's time for
today's feast to begin!
Bring on the bacchanalia
of bloodshed!
Thanks for the invitation.
This should be a lot of fun.
So this is a killing game?
Our dear headmistress
loves playing around with
our lives, doesn't she?
You ready, Julie?
Ja.
It's Miyabi!
Oh, thank goodness!
Wait, hold on!
What, but why?
[gasps]
Guys, watch this.
Miyabi?
You see?
I'm a whole lot stronger now.
What do you think, Tor?
[MIYABI]
I wanted to be stronger,
so I could catch up to the rest.
So I could stand
before him, too.
And so I could
be true to myself.
[JULIE]
Next time: "Killing Game."
Hey, Tor.
Watch this, okay?