[water running]
[MIYABI]
I froze.
In that moment I was helpless,
a liability for everyone else.
[sighs]
[GIRL]
Trouble concentrating?
You could barely focus
while we were sparring earlier.
[faucet squeaks]
Well, don't beat yourself up.
Nothing useful ever
comes from that.
Thanks, Tomoe.
Gloomy doesn't suit you.
We'd rather you be the
happy girl we all know and love.
Whadaya mean. Love?
[gasps]
[sighs]
[faucet squeaks]
[TOMOE]
Is something wrong?
Mmm.
No, it's nothing.
[TOR]
Blue as far as the eye can see.
How are you feeling?
Are you all right?
Ja.
I'm fine.
Thanks.
[GIRL] Hey, what do think
training camp'll be like?
[GIRL 2]
I brought my swimsuit.
You guys are gonna flip out!
It's, like,
the cutest thing ever!
I'm sorry, Tor.
Here we are,
headed off to a seaside
summer camp and I'm--
It isn't your fault that it's
hot and you got seasick.
Besides, there's no way this is
just your average summer camp.
So you should rest while
you have the chance.
Ja.
That's a good idea.
Your lap is comfortable.
So, nice.
[breathing softly]
Seeing Julie like this,
she reminds me of
some adorable little critter.
[chuckles]
[MIYABI]
Uh, Tor.
Hey. What's up, Miyabi?
Is Julie feeling okay?
Uh, Yeah.
I think the fresh air
has helped a little.
It's better than being
cooped up inside, anyway.
Yeah, I bet.
She looks pretty comfortable.
It's got to be hot over there.
Want to come and sit
in the shade with us?
What?
The shade?
Well. It would be
nice to cool off.
Ahh!
[gasps]
Hey, are you all right?
Come on, Tor.
Tsukimi wants to see us.
[TOR]
Are we there already?
Miyabi?
Yes, here.
I'm coming!
[MIYABI thinking]
What the heck am I doing?
[RITO] Now for an
important announcement!
All of you will be
swimming the rest of the way
to the training camp, which
is located on that island!
[STUDENTS]
What?
There's no way.
You've got to be kidding.
You mean
you're really serious?
'Course I am!
Oh. And as a part of
your special training,
you'll be swimming
in your uniforms, 'kay?
It should be a piece of
cake for you Exceeds!
I think I understand.
[giggles]
[TORA]
This is so Sakuya can sit back
and observe all of her
little lab rats at once.
[RITO]
This is your ultimate goal.
The "X" marks the training camp
building right in
the middle, seeee?
Are you guys fired up
about this, or what?
Oh.
Just in case you forgot, I
wanted to remind you about
the Rite of Sublimation
at the end of the term.
If you leveled up,
good for you.
But if you're one of those
sad-panda cubby-cubs
who didn't make the cut, try
not to drag your Duo down.
All right?
[TATSU grunting]
[TOMOE thinking]
Miyabi.
[rumbling]
[STUDENTS gasping]
Well?
Time to get moving!
[STUDENTS screaming]
Doing okay, Julie?
Ja.
But it looks like we've fallen
pretty far behind everyone else.
We'll catch up with the
rest of the class in no time.
You just hang on
real tight for me, okay?
Ja.
[helicopter blades pattering]
Tor, what's that sound?
Hi, Tor!
Up here!
Trying to pick out just
the right bathing suit
threw me way off schedule!
[TOR]
Lilith?
I think I can take it
from here, Sarah.
Miss, what do you mean?
Wait! No!
[laughing]
Oh, Tor!
Your future darling
bride-to-be has arrived!
My, my. Aren't you sweet?
Just look how easily you blush!
Stop. I'm not blushing.
Please get away from him.
He's my Duo and you
should respect that.
[LILITH]
Oh?
Let me guess.
You don't know how to swim.
As Tor's Duo, you should do your
best not to slow him down.
[giggles]
We don't have time for
any of this right now.
We have to get
over to the island.
You have got a point there.
Tell you what.
I'll race you!
We might as well
have a little fun!
[TOR]
Fun?
[TOR panting]
I knew swimming here wasn't
going to be a walk in the park.
But this is downright brutal.
[giggles]
I won, no question.
I'm sorry you had to carry me.
[TOR]
It's okay, Julie.
I just need to rest for
a few minutes, that's all.
Take as much time as you need.
The swim over here made my
panties soggy and uncomfortable.
[TOR] If I were you,
I'd get out of them
and let them dry off then.
Whoa! Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
[JULIE]
Oh.
You meant over there.
[TOR]
Yeah.
But be sure not to
wander too far off.
[JULIE]
Ja.
What a little weirdo.
[sighs]
[LILITH]
That's much better, isn't it?
Yeah, the shade is nice.
But sooner or later you'll
get hot too, won't you?
You don't have to
worry about me.
I'm doing this for you
because I really want to.
Although if it would
make you feel any better
I suppose there is something
you could do for me.
Sure.
It's only fair that
I return the favor.
Yeah.
So for my reward.
What?
Your kiss.
No! No, no, no!
I don't really need the shade!
But I appreciate the thought!
[JULIE whimpering]
Julie!
[panting]
What's going on?
I was trying to dry them off.
But then the wind came
and blew them away.
[sighs]
Which means you don't...
Tor.
I don't think you should
look at me right now.
[birds chirping]
[TOMOE]
You okay, Miyabi?
We're almost there.
Um, right.
I'm just slow.
It feels like no matter
what we're doing,
I'm always holding you back.
Now that's plain ridiculous.
[MIYABI screams]
Oh! Miyabi!
[MIYABI] Everyone else is
probably way ahead of us now.
[TOMOE]
It's okay.
I don't think there's
anything wrong
with moving at our own pace.
I'm soaked, too.
I'm so sorry, Tomoe.
I just--
[TOMOE]
Stop right there.
What's the matter?
[TOMOE]
You're my partner, Miyabi.
If you truly feel that
disappointed in yourself,
you're also disappointed in
me because I'm your Duo.
That's not what I--
[TOMOE]
You, Miyabi Hotaka,
are the partner that I
chose above all others.
[sighs]
Yeah! Perfect!
Now we can rinse off all
that salt from the ocean!
Feels great!
[TOR] Looks like that's
where the training camp is.
[LILITH]
It's going to be dark soon,
so we'd better get going.
Wait. Hold on a second.
Hm?
Yeah, what is it?
[fabric tearing]
[TOR] I know this
isn't exactly ideal.
But it's probably better than
going barefoot the entire way.
Oh, Tor, they're perfect!
That's why you're
my future husband!
And if you change your
mind, my Duo partner, too!
[JULIE gasps]
Hey, Tor.
I think this path
looks easier to walk.
[gasps]
[TOR gurgles]
What were those things?
Those are Kunai.
A type of throwing
knife used by ninjas.
Don't tell me it's those guys.
[gasps]
They have Blazes?
Hurry, Miyabi!
I'm coming!
Miyabi!
Ah!
They're everywhere!
[grunts and struggles]
[TOMOE thinking]
Bastards.
They're using the terrain
to get the upper hand.
[grunts]
Watch out, Tomoe!
[MIYABI]
Why?
--[grunting]
--[blades slashing]
[MIYABI thinking]
Why do I always freeze?
[screams]
[gasps]
[MIYABI thinking]
What would Tor do?
Blaze on!
[whimpers]
Miyabi.
[shouting]
--[grunting]
--[metal clashing]
[TOR thinking]
Who the hell are these guys?
Watch out!
They attacked us
in here so they
could use these trees
like a kind of cage.
Good thinking.
I don't remember
asking you to help me.
Ja. I'm doing this
because I really want to.
[laughs]
So then, what should our
next move here be, I wonder?
A little more space
to move around
sure would have been nice.
In that case, jump
straight up in the air.
What?
Roger that.
Blaze on!
No way.
Is this the power of a Level 3?
It's incredible!
Now.
Let's dance, shall we?
Haaaaaa!
Damn!
Who are these people
wielding Blazes?
Where did they come from?
[grunting]
[groaning]
It's time for me to end this!
[gasps]
Imari!
I guess now you know.
Long time no see.
Hi, Tor.
Yeah, hi.
It's been a while.
It has.
Now that we've caught up, would
you mind moving your hand?
[TOR]
Huh?
It's still there.
Pervert.
So, to all the students
from the main campus,
welcome to Koryo Academy's
branch school.
A mock battle might not
be the most polite way
to greet visiting students,
but please forgive us.
Consider it seaside summer camp
done the Koryo Academy way.
There you have it!
Joint training has
officially begun.
And we're thrilled you're here!
Good luck.
And cheers!
[STUDENTS]
Cheers!
[TATSU grunting]
[laughs]
[FEMALE STUDENTS giggling]
He's really my favorite!
Mm!
[loud eating]
[TOR] I had no clue
there was a branch school.
I was surprised when I
first found out about it.
The students who were defeated
in the opening screening rite
were told we could
attend the branch school
if that's what we wanted.
The training and environment
are incredibly rigorous,
but I gotta say, I've enjoyed
every second of it.
I can see that.
[IMARI] So, how have
things been with you?
Oh.
With me?
[JULIE]
It's like it's their last meal.
All of the meat was taken
as soon as it got there.
Everyone did spend the day
swimming and fighting
so I'm sure they're starving.
Do you want one of mine?
Ja.
Thank you very much.
Oh, it's hot!
[muffled]
This is very good.
It's so juicy.
And big.
[TOR]
Uh...
[JULIE muffled]
It's delicious.
[LILITH]
Tor.
Huh?
Here you go.
Is this all for me?
Don't be daft.
I'm asking you to
feed me because
both of my hands are occupied.
Ahhhh.
That's right, say "ah."
This is actually pretty tasty.
Wait, was there some
misunderstanding
because I remember
asking Tor to feed me.
Open up.
Say, "ah."
Ahh--
So good!
Stop doing that!
Are you even
listening to me?
[BOTH laughing]
Headmistress.
Look, I was wrong about you.
At first I thought you
were so coldhearted.
But I had no idea that
you planned to give
Imari and the others
another chance.
I'm really grateful
to you for that.
I just wanted to say thank you.
Then you still have some
misapprehension about me.
What?
I can assure you that
everything I do is in service of
finding the talent that
the Dorn Agency requires.
I have done nothing
to merit any thanks.
Well, then, good evening.
Tor Kokonoe.
I desire one thing
and one thing only.
That this path I'm on,
will one day lead me
to Absolute Duo.
[FEMALE STUDENT] The way you
fought back there was amazing!
[FEMALE STUDENT 2]
It's no wonder you
got into the main school!
I'm not that impressive.
You most certainly are!
Every day I find something
new to admire in you.
Um, Thanks a lot, Tomoe.
I'm going to go get some food!
[MIYABI gasps]
Huh?
Sorry 'bout that!
No, please go ahead.
So, you're the talk of
the training camp.
I heard about how bravely you
fought to save Tomoe earlier.
Well.
There was a point where my
instincts just took over.
And that was
mostly because you--
[gasps]
Huh?
What was that you
just said about me?
Uh.
It's nothing.
Of course.
It's because Tor has been
there for me so many times...
that I feel...
I feel like...
Hey, Miyabi!
Tor, what are you
doing over there?
Coming!
Let's go!
'Kay!
[MIYABI thinking]
Now I know.
That what I'm
feeling for Tor is love.
True Love.
[MAN] The Unit is now
completely calibrated.
All that's left is to
move onto the final stage.
But, of course,
in order to do that
I require one last component.
[loud chewing]
And you'd like me to obtain it.
Is that right?
[MAN]
Yes.
And there's no reason for you to
report this to the higher-ups.
They are just as
curious as we are
to find out how
powerful this thing is.
The test results should be more
than enough to satisfy them.
The test.
Assess and be assessed, is it?
And what will the
codename be this time?
[chuckles]
A competition.
Let's call it Selection.
What do you think?
[sinister laugh]
[grunting]
That should do it.
I need a favor that
might seem strange,
but will actually help
us bunk together
for the rest of our time
here at summer camp.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I'd be happy to help.
Ja.
About what happened today.
I now know that it taught me
a very important
lesson about life.
An ounce of prevention's
worth a pound of cure.
Please hang on to these
in case I need them?
These?
Tor.
Is it necessary
to look at them?
[sputtering]
Sorry.
"These" were not
what I was expecting.
[IMARI]
It's summer!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[IMARI]
Time for swimsuits!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[IMARI]
And hot springs!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Next time, "Selection."
Plus, a wardrobe malfunction!