I never realized you had such
a sweet tooth, Henrietta.
Well lately... the tea has
been tasting kind of bitter,
so I've been
adding... more sugar.
It tastes better that way.
I know... From here on out your
nickname is gonna be Sweetie.
Hehe, come on, Triela.
Haha, I'm just
kidding around.
I think you all
know the truth.
What?
We're all going to die!
We'll all die empty and
alone! It's the truth!
Marco's so angry at me
that I wish I could die now
and get it over with...
Why can't I just die?!
If you want to die
then kill yourself!
I should never have
bothered saving you!
Henrietta.
Did you ever find
anyone to take us?
Huh?
Remember... You wanted to
watch the meteor shower tonight
but thought
it'd be better
to watch from the
training grounds.
You said all the light
pollution from Rome
would make it harder to
see anything from here.
Oh, that's right.
Sorry! I
have to go.
So who's
gonna take us?
Oh... I took
care of it.
I already asked
Jose to take us.
Here.
Look at this.
Okay.
See the double star? That's
the Rigel binary system.
It's known as the
'Left Leg of the Giant.'
Jose. Do you
think Angelica
will be in the
hospital for awhile?
Yeah.
Everyone's...
worried about her.
Why don't you go
visit her tomorrow?
Okay.
Must be all the light
pollution coming from Rome...
A hundred years ago I'm sure
you could see every star
in the sky
from here.
We'll be at the training
grounds tomorrow.
We should have a great view of
the meteor shower from there.
Uh, Henrietta.
Yes, Jose?
I'm sorry... Some... some
urgent work just came up.
I won't be able to
take you tomorrow.
Oh that's...
That's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure I can find
someone else to take us.
See, I told you.
But everything was planned
out until yesterday.
We're not watching the
meteor shower tomorrow?
Hmm, If worse comes to worse,
we could go up on the roof
and see at least
a few of them.
Alright then.
Tomorrow I'll
find someone else
to take us to the
training grounds.
Really?
We have been looking
forward to it for awhile.
Hear that?
Yeah.
Good night.
Night.
Don't worry.
I'm sure Triela will figure
something out for us.
Yeah.
But all I wanted...
was to watch the shooting
stars with Jose.
I think you all
know the truth.
What?
We're all going to die!
We'll all die empty and
alone! It's the truth!
Marco's so angry at me
that I wish I could die now
and get it over with...
Why can't I just die?!
I tell ya... the things I
do for Henrietta sometimes.
You spoil her too much.
She seems to think you
can fix anything Triela.
I don't mind really. I'll
just have to make it happen.
Is she visiting
Angelica?
Nice shooting.
Thank you.
Hey, Jean.
What's up?
Is Angelica... do you
think she's gonna die?
I doubt she has
long to live.
A cyborg's life
span is limited.
The question is how to best
utilize the time you have.
Don't worry. You still
have a long while to go.
Okay.
Angelica?
Henrietta.
Thanks for visiting me.
The flowers are beautiful.
How do you feel?
My body feels heavy...
I've been having a hard time
concentrating on anything...
But other than
that, I feel okay...
I'm sure in a few
days I'll feel better
and be back at work.
We can't wait for
you to come back.
Thanks.
I think that's the Chief's
dog... I saw him earlier.
Angelica.
Is there something
wrong...? Are you okay?
Pero.
What Angelica?
The name of... the
dog I used to have.
Angelica.
Pero.
Henrietta... When
did you get here?
Huh?
What beautiful flowers.
Thanks so much.
Where's Marco?
Is he not here?
No, he's not here yet.
He must be busy with work.
Claes.
Hospitals really
aren't so bad...
I mean sometimes it
gets really boring,
but I do get
visitors everyday.
Someone just came
by... It was...
Angelica...
Angelica... I just
want to say I'm sorry
for what I said
to you earlier.
No, I should apologize...
After all you did save
my life back there...
If only I could
have been stronger
like the rest of you girls.
I'm not as strong
as you may think...
I am afraid to die...
and I don't like pain.
I think I probably draw
pictures and read books
everyday because I
don't want to feel like
I'm wasting my life...
I'm afraid, and I don't want to
have any regrets before I die.
Know what I mean?
So are you going
to stay up tonight?
Should I?
Yeah. There's a meteor shower,
and you'll probably be able
to see it from
your window here.
Really?
If you can,
listen to this song while
you watch it... 'Kay?
Sure.
Excuse me, sir.
Huh...? Oh,
hello, Triela.
What's up?
I was hoping you
could supervise us
while we watch
the meteor shower
at the training
grounds tonight.
Eh?
Jose backed out.
Said he's busy.
Sorry, but as you can
see, we're swamped today.
We have to translate all these
EU public safety documents
into Italian by
tomorrow morning.
Then why don't you let me
help you translate them?
I'm fluent in 3
languages you know.
Marco.
I, uh...
What is it?
I went to visit Angelica
this morning and...
she suddenly...
she remembered a dog she
used to have named Pero.
I see... I'll
notify the engineers.
They'll come by to
run some tests on her
and see what's
going on.
Uh... Do you know
where her dog is now?
No, I don't.
Maybe we could go
looking for it.
There'd be no point in that.
Marco!
Is there something
else, Henrietta?
You have to see her...
Just go visit Angelica.
The doctors have taken
all the necessary precautions.
If something happens,
they'll notify me.
Please just
visit her.
It's pointless,
Henrietta.
There's nothing I
can do for her now.
You don't have
to do anything.
Just be by her side.
She wants that.
Please, Marco.
Henrietta... Are
you afraid of dying?
I'm not afraid
of anything.
Especially if it means
fighting to protect Jose.
You don't resent what these
doctors have done to you?
Giving you nothing
but a mechanical body,
a handful of bullets and a
life too short to enjoy?
All of us girls have accepted
what we've been made to do.
So if you at all pity
or feel sorry for us...
then you're
mistaken.
I realize this may be the
conditioning saying this...
but I don't
mind... Even so.
I'm not
afraid to die.
And I'm certain Angelica
feels the same way!
Hi Marco.
Did I wake you?
No. It's alright...
I'm... gonna try
really hard next time.
Lay down.
Yes, sir.
I don't see any.
Maybe it's just
not time yet.
It'll be soon...
Keep watching.
We'd have been better off
if we were further away
from the lights of Rome.
But I guess our eyesight is
the best it can possibly be.
I saw one!
Really? Where?
It was right over
there. Oh! Another one!
Look Triela! Up there!
You're missing it!
Alright, Rico...
Calm down.
I'm sorry but this
is the first time
I've ever seen
a shooting star!
Marco.
I'm glad you're
here with me.
Did you know there's supposed
to be a meteor shower tonight?
Claes said I should be
able to see some of them
from the window here.
Watching it all by myself
wouldn't be much fun.
That's true.
It's so quiet.
As the world gets more
and more complicated...
and there's so much
to think about...
it's good to let your
mind empty like this
every once in a while.
I wish Angelica
could see this too.
Oh she is... I wonder
if she's listening
to the Ninth while
she watches it.
Wait, do you mean
Beethoven's Ninth?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, it's definitely
the perfect symphony
for such a
beautiful night.
Is this
it...?
[Humming Beethoven]
Like that?
♪ Freude, schöner Götterfunken,
Tochter aus Elysium... ♪
Like that.
Okay!
♪ Wir betreten feuertrunken,
Himmlische, dein Heiligtum! ♪
♪ Deine Zauber binden wieder,
Was die Mode streng geteilt. ♪
I saw one!
Me too.
So beautiful.
Yes it is.
Hey Marco.
Yeah?
The pasta story.
Hmm?
Will you please read me
the Pasta story again?
Sure. Just
a minute.
Once upon a time, there
was a kingdom made of pasta.
In this kingdom there lived
a prince who loved pasta,
and would eat it for
every meal of every day.
Alphonso,
what's so funny?
It's just the thought
of these little girls
who can kill terrorists
and speak three languages.
And here they are singing
Beethoven in the bitter cold.
It's a shame they
have to be cyborgs.
Then Prince Pasta
said to Princess Pizza,
This dragon is...
A-Angelica?
A-Are you asleep? Angelica?