She's my sister.
We're always together,
so we're known on the
inside as 'fratello'.
Fratello... It means
siblings... brother and sister.
Some people crack jokes about
it, but what are you gonna do?
It's as close to the
truth as you can get.
[Marco] Chief, we strongly
believe he has knowledge of the
Republican Faction's weapons
smuggling... I suggest, for
safety, we might want to take
down all of their safehouses.
Fine... I want the
Hilshire-Triela fratello
to cover the
southern safehouse.
Sir, consider it
taken care of.
[Marco] But the
Jean-Rico team...
They're going to need
at least some kind of support,
don't you think?
I'll take some Section 2
members and we can cover
the building's perimeter...
But I'd want at least two more
fratello to help us
secure the location.
Jean, this is Hilshire.
Look... We've got the southern
safehouse locked down,
but there's an issue...
Our target isn't anywhere
that we can find...
It is possible that he's
already moved down to your end.
Double-check that.
[Hilshire] Roger. I'll work over
those that are still breathing.
I'll notify you the second
I figure anything out.
[Phone] What's going on over
there? Somebody answer me!
Can Jose... handle this?
Uh, Chief... In my
opinion, they're not ready
for group operations.
[Marco]
Jean, let it go.
Well I think they are.
I'm adding Jose and Henrietta
to the Jean-Rico team...
You got that... Jean?
Sir.
[Jean] We got a message from
the Hilshire-Triela team.
Looks like we are the
ones favored to win today.
Just get a positive ID
on the target first.
And listen, if
he's not with them,
I want you to
let them go.
Don't do
anything. Got it?
[Jose] Let's go.
[Hilshire] Ferro, is the
entrance clear?
Alfonso and I have
covered the front.
Amadeo and Giorgio have the
back. The only other way for
this mark to get out is through
the window you're staring at.
[Jean]
Wait for my orders.
[Ferro] Affirmative.
[Jean] Rico, focus on
any shadows you see
behind the blinds.
Yes sir.
[Head Baddie] The southern
hideout's been attacked.
[All Baddies]
What?!
[Head Baddie] It would
seem that someone
has coming looking
for him, gentlemen.
Then that means...
that they might...
They might
end up here.
If I understand
it correctly...
they were attacked
by a young girl.
A girl?
Yeah.
I know...
it sounds crazy, but, recently
I've been hearing rumors of
a secret agency
that's been training
little girls
as assasins.
[doorbell rings]
Who is it, Louie?
You won't believe this, but
it's a guy in a suit and a...
[Head Baddie]
A what?
Uh... A little girl.
Don't open it.
I'll get them
outta your hair.
Louie! I said don't!
Good morning, sir.
I apologize for intruding like
this. Do you have a minute?
No. What do
you want?
Just a few moments
of your time.
I am a reporter
from Libero Italia.
What is it you're reporting?
I heard that Mr. Scallo of
the Costelo Company was here...
...and I would love
to get an exclusive.
Yeah well, there ain't
nobody here by that name,
so good luck finding
your interview.
Wait, I'm... positive that
he's in this building.
Yeah? And I just told you that
you got the wrong room, chief.
You hard of hearing?
No...
Then maybe it's a learning
disorder. Your guy ain't here!
Sorry, I...
Now, get lost before
I pop your eyes out
and make your
sister watch!
[Submachine Baddie] Louie,
what's going on--
Brother...
You planning on visiting
every hospital in Italy?
No, uh...
I'm not.
I've already made
my decision.
Why does it have
to be children?
These kids have been
through enough already.
It's the agency's call.
The physical alterations,
the brainwashing...
All the conditioning seems
to take much better,
the younger
the subject.
This is the work of the Social
Welfare Agency, isn't it?
Yes.
[Doctor] Our government's
created quite an impressive
organization. To see it
actively aiding the seriously
injured, I mean, I never
thought they'd follow through.
Dr. Masi, we
came because...
We have heard that your
facility is housing
a very seriously
injured girl.
Yes.
It was tragic... She's in
desperate need of your help.
Last week, her
family was massacred.
But the monsters
kept her alive.
Throughout the night,
the poor girl was
brutally assaulted.
And all the while, her
family members' bodies
lay sprawled,
lifeless, around her.
She's confided in us
thoughts of suicide.
[Ferro] Have you come up
with a name for her yet?
[Jose]
Henrietta.
Henrietta it is, then.
Thank you.
Once she gets used
to the facility,
we'll move her into
a room with Rico.
She's awake.
[Jose] I see
you're awake.
You
thirsty?
No,
thanks.
My name
is Jose.
You're up
early.
Did you get
any sleep?
No.
Why not?
You told me to get
proficient quickly, Jose.
Stop it.
[Jose] Don't use your
sight during practice.
You'll never have time
to use it in combat,
so don't get spoiled by it.
Just shoot in the general
direction of the target.
At close range,
it won't matter
what part of their body
you lodge a bullet,
it'll still keep them
from going very far.
Average, Jose.
[Head Baddie]
Hey--
Throw your grenade!
Take him.
[Worker] Good. Now, when you
and your pal there is finished
down there, I got, like,
two tons of rebar I need hauled
all the way
over to site B.
[Jose]
Now you've done it.
Ferro... The
mission has failed.
I Repeat: Mission
has failed.
[Ferro] Roger.
We're on our way.
Yeah.
Henrietta, why did
you lose control?
Uh...
This isn't like you...
I've never seen you
lose it like that.
Your arm's been hit.
[Jose] Are you okay?
[Henrietta]
Yes...
Jose, we're here.
Ferro. The witness isn't here.
Judging by their reaction,
I'd say he's hiding
in the building somewhere.
I'll put people on it...
Alfonso, Amadeo...
start at the rooftop
and work your way down.
Giorgio, watch the perimeter.
[Jose] Let's go home.
Please, don't
shoot! I surrender!
[Jean] Jose,
you need to increase her
level of conditioning...
You've got to put a bigger
collar on your hunting dog.
I think you're
wrong about that.
Too much conditioning will...
will shorten her lifespan.
[Jean] Then we just prep a new
patient once she's used up.
You're too emotionally attached
to a tool of the trade.
Jean... enough.
She may have a few issues...
But she's an
excellent assassin...
It would be wasteful to dispose
of Henrietta... Anyway...
We got what we came for,
and lost none of our own...
You need to learn to take a
broader perspective of things.
Sir.
Jose... As you know, each
handler is responsible for
the actions of his
own girl in the field.
Now, if you think
Henrietta can work with
little conditioning, then I'd
like for you to give it a shot.
However, further mistakes
are inexcusable...
Please make certain this is a
lesson she understands.
[Jose]
Yes, sir.
[Jose] Henrietta stayed
as quiet as she could
when I first brought
her to the agency.
Not that I can
blame her.
Watching her family
get murdered.
How do you get over
something like that?
How could she wrap her head
around the fact that she,
out of everybody,
she survived.
When I first set eyes on
her at the national hospital,
her mind and her body were
ragged and worn-through.
I chose Henrietta
as my partner.
Was it because I wanted
to do something nice?
Or did I choose
her out of pity?
Whatever it was, I knew
I wanted to help her.
[Triela]
Henrietta!
Rico just told me...
You flipped your lid
out there today.
I-I couldn't control it.
I just snapped.
Triela... I don't
know what to do.
[Triela]
Don't sweat it.
Hey -- I know! We can go
have a drink in Claes' room.
A drink?
Yeah. She's got
the best tea,
and I swear she puts
magic in her cakes.
You just wanted to make him
proud of you. That's all.
[Henrietta] Yeah...
I guess so...
But Triela...
Isn't that the only
thing any of us can do?
We all seek approval.
And if I were him...
that kind of devotion would
make me feel uncomfortable.
[Jose] Let's go.
Right.
[Henrietta]
Jose...
Is your arm hurting?
I only...
I just wanted to
help you, Jose.
[Jose] We'll have a
doctor take a look
at that arm as soon
as we get back.