Hey, Elenora... Do You
suppose they'll let us
drive this car
onto Sicily Island?
Let me check my
little book here...
And yes - There's a
ferry that takes cars
leaving out of
Reggio Di Calabria.
Without you, I'd probably
have to swim across.
And just if you're interested,
this road we're on
was the same road
the ancient Romans
used to attack the
Greeks in Sicily.
Please tell me you don't
have the color of my boxers
in that book too...
We'll be staying in a
hotel just by the port.
If anything happens,
we can be here quick.
Anyone ever told you you
worry too much, Ferro?
You know what
happened to Elsa...
We could all stand to
be more cautious...
Henrietta...
I want you to make sure
nothing happens to Jose.
Yes, ma'am.
This house is nice.
I hope. My parents
spent a fortune on it.
We used to vacation
here in the summers.
Your family?
Even Jean?
Yeah, he was here, too.
But Right now, I'm
spending time with you...
Step out onto the terrace.
We should come back here
after the seasons change.
Sicily in summer
is breathtaking.
You mean you would bring me
back for another holiday?
As often
as you like.
Henrietta... I want
you to give me your case
and the SIG
on your belt.
Come on.
I can't. These
are things I need
if I'm going to protect
you like I was ordered.
We're here
under the guise
that I am a reporter
and you are my neice.
A normal girl
shouldn't be carrying
these kinds of
things with her.
A normal
girl... normal?
That's right.
Gimme a break
Lucky dogs.
What kind of work
do they think they
can get done here?
Living here, you could
begin to believe
that the world ends
where the water begins.
You should quit Section One
and become a tour guide.
I guess I'm the one who gets
to point out the irony here.
The cyborgs were
designed to protect us...
and now we're
protecting them.
Stunning observation.
But it's hardly the time.
Perhaps we should focus on
why we're here and not how.
Yeah, yeah. I've
heard it before.
I thought they...
They're from Section Two...
Why are we hiding
from our own?
Just avoiding
trouble.
It comes in all
shapes and sizes.
Okay....
Maybe they're
not home.
Hey, there...
Please, don't go
for your gun...
We're also from the
Social Welfare Agency...
I'm Pietro Fermi and Elenora
Gabrielli from Section One...
Triela told us about you.
Section One, huh?
That's right,
reporter on vacation.
The vacation part's
real. What do you want?
Nothing big, I'm handling
a certain incident
for our section...
May we come inside...?
I'm getting a
bit of a chill.
Sure. Come on in.
Henrietta...
But... There are no weapons
allowed in this house.
I'll take them for you.
We're on holiday and
the smell of gun oil
puts us both
in a work mood.
What next?
You gonna unstrap my family
jewels and confiscate them?
And leave your mouth at the
door, if you don't mind.
I thought that the Elsa case
had already been closed.
It was.
So basically, you're
just waiting to find
the terrorists that
did this and grab 'em.
That's the official word.
But there's something...
Something doesn't feel
right about this case.
Our superior didn't
order us out here.
Pietro... Why
didn't you tell me-
so the director
didn't send us?
No, I told him that my
grandmother in Naples
fell ill... So this is half
personal, half business.
Why did you follow us?
Triela told us that if
we wanted to learn more
about fratello relationships,
then we should look to you.
Okay...
Henrietta?
Would you mind making us
up some dinner for everyone?
Okay.
That's great. She does all
the housework, too, I see.
Yeah. But She practices
cooking in her dorm room.
I wouldn't expect
anything tasty.
Elenora...
Oh, right... I'll
supervise the cooking.
I assume that the
respect she has for you
is due to your
conditioning of her.
Every cyborg requires
conditioning to be usable...
and Henrietta is
no exception.
But I don't increase her
conditioning to make her loyal.
I have never forced any of the
affection she feels for me.
Tell me, what difference
does that make...?
Just because it's not
you don't it as much
doesn't make it all
sunshine you know.
Believe me, I agree...
I realize that we're
only using these girls
to further our own agenda...
I do realize that.
So, what's for dinner?
Just, uh...
Tomato soup pasta.
Is that it?
Yes.
Maybe we could add a
few more ingredients.
But I can't--
I don't know how to
cook without a recipe.
It's no problem.
I have some cooking notes
somewhere. Here they are!
Tomato soup but with tuna
in place of the pasta...
and on the side,
marinated seafood
with vegetable caponata...
and some olives and cheese...
How's
that sound?
That's great... It's
like a magical notebook.
No magic
here, sorry...
I just happen to have one
of the worst memories
of anyone I know...
And As we know, all
successful jobs are--
Are all comprised of many
smaller and much simpler tasks.
Right... But, uh...
Where'd you hear that?
Oh, I... I can't remember...
We should go to the market.
Yeah, you're right...
We've got some hungry men
waiting in the other room.
Yeah.
You really like him. But
what kind of feeling is it?
Is it the love
for a brother?
Or does the agency determine
how you feel about things?
It doesn't matter to me. I
just know that I feel good.
That's kind of normal.
But I still have to do what
they want. The agency.
What I do for Jose though,
is what I want to do for him.
It sounds to me like
you're in love with him.
I guess. I mean, you're in
love with Pietro, aren't you?
Uh, no. I'm not.
You understand,
a man and a woman
don't have to be in
love to work together.
They can just be partners.
But you're tall and beautiful
and you have pretty hair.
I think he
suits you well.
He's better off with a tougher
woman of sorts. Trust me.
I don't think so.
Sorry, it's true.
Henrietta!
You gotta keep in mind how
vulnerable you girls are
when you're not
concentrating.
Here.
Thank you.
Uh, didn't you
have a purse?
I'll go get it.
Wait...
There he is.
Give it back.
How did you get here?
Give me back my purse...
and you won't get hurt.
I don't think so, missy...
Now get outta here!
Wait... How did you--
Let... Let go-
Police!
Give that girl back her
things or I'm taking you in.
I don't have
her stuff...
Just tell this
freak to let me go!
Henrietta.
Drop him.
Now, give it
back to her.
What are you
talking about?
Playing dumb...?
I said I would let you go
if you gave the girl
her purse back.
You stink of whiskey, which
puts you at DUI already.
I guess I'll let the
boys downtown know
just how thorough
they need to search you.
Was it really
that important?
The camera that Jose
gave me is inside.
I couldn't just
let it go.
Oh.
Elenora? The badge that you
pulled out, was that the, uh...
The magical
notebook, yeah.
Back there, you were the
toughest woman ever.
Back there, you were
the scariest girl ever.
So You don't have any
suspicions about Elsa's death?
The question is, do
you have suspicions?
Yeah.
I do.
The whole story sounds... just
way too convenient for me.
You thinking... What?
A conspiracy?
An agency trained man
and his cyborg are killed.
No investigation, but they
suddenly know who did it.
What do you think?
As enhanced as the cyborgs
are in their abilities
and their senses,
they're useless
if they aren't concentrating.
The fratello was ambushed
at night in the park.
It's not out of the
realm of possibility
that this happened the
way they say it did.
Jean told me the girls
are highly sensitive
to any danger that their
handler might be exposed to...
When I met Rico yesterday
she was the Aegis shield.
Nothing was
getting past her.
Each handler conditions
his own cyborg...
Elsa reacted, only
not fast enough.
I don't
like it.
Everyone in your department
is so quick to say
the cyborg did the
right thing...
And while I'm sure you
believe that...
Something about
this feels wrong.
I admit, the idea of cyborgs
disgusted me at first...
More than half of their
bodies are carbon framing,
fiber-optics, and artificially
bioengineered muscle...
But in the end, every
last one of them
is just a regular
adolescent girl...
And they come with the
whole gambit of emotions...
They seek approval, they can't
understand their feelings,
and they can't
cook worth a damn.
It seems like they
really liked the food.
After the all effort
you put into the meal,
how could they not...?
But Henrietta...
I want to tell you not to
run off like you did earlier.
Normally, little girls aren't
supposed to be violent
like that...
You understand?
You, too,
Elenora.
You're trying to make me into
more of a normal girl, too.
I can tell.
You are normal.
When we got here, Jose
took my weapons away.
He said that normal
girls don't carry them.
I know that he's right.
So are you. But am I...
Am I normal...?
I have strength...
I can kill with
my bare hands...
I bleed red, but the pain
always goes away quickly...
Sometimes I see things in my
head that have never happened.
I am a
cyborg...
I'll never be useful
as anything else...
To Jose I'll never be a
normal girl no matter--
No! You're wrong!
He thinks the
world of you...
He wants you to smile and to
enjoy everything that you can.
Elenora...
I understand now
how Elsa died.
Could you get Jose and
Pietro and meet me outside?
Please bring my
sidearm, too.
Can I please
hold my gun?
Wait.
Explain yourself first.
Pietro... Would you say
that Elsa loved Lauro?
I'd say so.
Jose, did you ever see
Lauro being nice to Elsa?
Not really. With him,
everything was always business.
That's how it all started...
What would happen if
you loved someone...
Loved them with
all your heart,
like you never
thought you could...
but you realized one
day that they would never,
ever feel that way for you?
If it were me...
I would kill that
person. And then...
I'd do this.
You can calm down now.
I wouldn't shoot.
How could I
kill myself
while you're this
wonderful, Jose?
You know that no one has
ever been this good to me.
I had
no idea.
She was serious when
she said she knew.
Talk about
a scare.
Jose, you knew the whole
time how Elsa died
and kept it
to yourself.
Explains your reaction when
I went to give her the gun.
So that was the secret behind
the two bullets they found.
It's worse than
that little girl
taking a bullet
for her handler.
You gonna
report this?
Oh c'mon...
You know Section
Two had to have
destroyed the
evidence by now...
This'll never be
more than a theory.
But the way Henrietta
acted with the gun--
She was responding to an
unconscious threat...
She knew why Elsa did
what she did.
Henrietta just
wanted us to know.
She seemed so innocent
this afternoon.
That's why it's hard to
wrap your mind around it.
Oh, yeah I forgot
to show you.
I did find something
interesting in Elsa's room.
A photo of Lauro.
All she ever got from him was
her name and his picture.
Must've been hard
for him to deal with,
all of that affection.
Your average Joe
couldn't stomach it.
Above all things,
you have to be someone the
girls can look up to...
In fact that's the
absolute least you can do.
What is it you wanted to
show me out here again?
But Lauro... Don't
you remember this park?
You brought me
here, to this park
and this is where you named
me... 'Elsa De Sica'.
Oh... You're
serious...?
I can't believe you'd
remember something like that.
It's such an important
day, I'd never forget it...
I'd never forget the beautiful
gift you have given me.
Are you done? Let's go.
We have an early morning.
I can't believe you
dragged me out here...
This is... where
you gave me life.
So long, Henrietta.
Yes, goodbye.
See ya.
Yeah.
So... Where would
you like to go first?
Sicily is full of
beautiful places.
Oh, really?
We'll leave whenever
you're ready...
And don't forget
your camera.
Okay!