What exactly have you been
doing this whole time?!
I've been here! The one
place you're too busy for!
I take care of
her! By myself!
Do you know how much
these hospital bills are?!
[Rico] Because of my sickness,
my parents argue constantly.
They try to do right.
Follow the doctor's orders.
And 'sign away on seventeen
separate documents'.
I've heard
that one a lot.
I had never left that hospital
room once in my whole life.
But then on my
birthday two years ago,
I got a new body and now I'm
free to move however I want to.
[Henrietta] Good
morning, Rico.
Oh, Good morning.
I was about to do my laundry.
You wanna come with?
Yeah.
[Rico] I really like my new
life here at the agency.
Everyone here
is so nice.
As long as I follow the
rules and do like I'm told,
I know they'll keep being
nice. It's the... It's like...
The quiet
morning air
and the smell of fresh
laundry detergent
coming across it. The sky
and the clouds and the sun.
And my
own body.
No matter how
hard you look,
you just can't find any of
those things in a hospital bed.
[Triela] Henrietta, do you know
what our schedule is today?
I think we're training at the
outdoor shooting range later.
Sounds fun.
I thought you didn't
like shooting practice...
Anything is better
than sitting through
another one of
Hilshire's boring lectures.
Triela. Page thirty-six. Begin
from Shylock's line please.
I don't get what you mean,
but it's fun to sit and watch.
There's still so much I
don't know. It's interesting.
[Claes] Yes, you're interested
in everything. We know, Rico.
So, Henrietta, do you have
any favorite classes so far?
How about music?
If I'm not mistaken,
I've heard you around
playing a violin.
[Claes] Have you always
liked the violin?
Did you ask for lessons?
Not really...
I like it...
But Jose suggested it...
He got sorta mad at me--
So, even though
you never asked,
he's pushing violin
lessons on you?
Not pushing... I really
like playing the violin.
I didn't mean
it like that.
Jose thinks the world
of you, Henrietta.
Do you think so?
That was
terrible.
Don't just listen to me-
hear what I have to say.
You need to be
more flexible.
Yes, sir.
Now, fire ten
second bursts.
Raise your
arms higher
and line up the front
sight with the rear.
Only when you have your
line of sight do you fire.
Hilshire, you're
not actually trying
to instruct
Triela are you?
Not much. She always
fares better on her own.
With a brother like you
what choice does she have?
Speaking of,
where's Angelica?
Her implants aren't
functioning well,
so I'm letting her rest.
She'll be out of commission for
a while, during recalibration.
How about some
news on our next job?
Some hot shot politician.
He made an inquiry regarding
'personal business.'
Of course,
that's just great...
I don't want these girls
wasting their talents
on meaningless jobs.
[Hilshire] Telling them
to kill the bad guys
and flush out the Republican
Faction's safehouses
is one thing.
'Personal business'
that's something else.
Anyway, sounds like a job
for Special Ops Section One.
Not us.
That's just the problem.
This politician is a big
supporter of all of us
over here in Cybernetics
Section Two.
We have to say yes.
You should always be
worried about those
who favor you
for no reason.
Lose your footing during the
real thing and you're dead.
Yes, sir.
We'll be there assembled and
on time, sir. Out... Jose...
We have a date for
the next mission.
You're gonna have to put
a hold on your training.
[Chief] Jean, if you'd run
down the plan for us...
[Jean] Thank
you, sir.
This is the mark, Congressman
Mascart of the Radical Party.
Our mission commences
one week from today
at the Villa
Gadd Hotel,
where the Congressman
will be staying.
Before each session
of Parliament,
he and his
secretaries set up here
and scour over documents
nearly twenty-four-seven.
He's staying in room number
two on the third floor.
So... we've booked
all of the other rooms
on that floor
anonymously...
You don't have to worry
about anyone coming up
during the operation...
The details are here,
but if you have questions...
now's the time.
Jean... Is this mission what
our congressman asked us to do?
Yes.
I've been told he and
Mascart oppose each other
in regards to the
amendment of the Conrad Act.
Mascart is very vocal in
his criticism of terrorism,
so we have
plenty of options
when it comes to
placing the blame.
[Jean] Hilshire
and Marco,
you two to gather our teams
and prep for departure.
We're on
top of it.
Hey, Ferro...
It almost seems like Mascart's
a criminal in all of this.
There's no 'almost' about
it. He is a criminal.
Which you don't seem to
have a problem with, Ferro.
Haven't you ever heard the
term 'love thy neighbor'?
Where in your little saying
does it tell you that
they're gonna love us back?
[Black Detective] You've
got no sense of romance.
[Alfonso] Maybe
you should teach her.
[Black Detective]
Ha, ha. Very funny.
[Jean] Here's
the plan, Rico.
The mark is staying in
that hotel across the street.
After a successful
assassination...
they'll find hair
and footprints...
This will lead them back to
the Republican Faction...
Today's a survey.
We'll check inside later.
[Rico]
Right.
But for now,
I want you to go and
check out the back entrance.
Tell me what you see.
Can I help you
with something?
You know this area out here
is for employees only.
Do you work here?
Uh-uh, I don't...
I was just...
Oh, yeah...
I get it.
You were looking for a
place to play your instrument.
What is it that you're
carrying? A violin, right?
Uh, yeah.
You can play it right
here if you want to.
I'd love to hear...
What kind of songs
do you like to play?
I, uh...
I can't play.
Oh, why not?
I'm not any good... and I
don't really know any songs.
So, you're not a musician yet.
You're still an apprentice...
Like me at the hotel.
My name is Emilio.
What's your name?
Rico.
Weird... I thought
that was a boy's name...
But in a cool way it
does kind of suit you...
I used to know a boy
named Rico once...
This boy seems to like
talking nicely to me.
I wonder if all boys
are like this one.
I'm not sure what I should
say to him. I'm nervous.
Yeah, my dad, he... just
kinda up and left me...
so now...
it's up to me
to make it on my
own in this world.
I see.
So, I told
you about my dad.
What does your
dad do for a living?
Uh... He's probably with the
city's waterworks bureau
or something.
Probably? You mean the two
of you don't live together?
No, I've been on my own
for a couple of years now.
Oh, you must live in
one of those dormitories
that they have at
the good schools.
Well, uh... It's
something like that.
Don't you ever
get lonely there,
never being able to see
your mother or father?
No, it's not that bad...
I have some friends there.
[Emillio]
Friends are good.
She's taking her time.
Yep.
She's incapable of doing
anything by herself.
So then I just told Daniel
right to his face, I said...
'I may be just a
poor kid now,
but someday I'll make it big
and laugh at all of you!'
...That's what I said,
I couldn't believe it.
Emilio?
Yeah?
You should get back to work.
You've been out here a while.
Is something wrong?
No, it's just...
It's time for me to get
back to where I live...
And you'll get in trouble if
you don't go back to work.
I guess
you're right.
I'm sorry.
Wait...
Rico!
I work
everyday,
so if you ever
wanna play a song,
come back I'd
like to hear it.
Okay...
Goodbye... Emilio.
Emilio, enough
of your slacking!
Daniel, you won't
believe what just happened!
What's that?
Just now, I met this cute
girl out here in the alley!
In the
alley? Huh...
Oh, yeah, she was
so nice to talk to.
She was blonde and
carried an Amati violin...
I think she'll come back
and play for me sometime.
Oh, yeah... Love
at first sight, kid?
Take my advice.
Forget about her.
What?!
Why?!
You think a cute girl
with an expensive violin
is interested
in you..?
The elite don't hang
with the help, kid.
You're
late, Rico.
Sorry.
Did you happen to
run into anybody?
No.
If you are
seen on a job,
it is your duty to kill who
sees you... Is this clear?
Yes, sir.
Henrietta, I
have a question.
What is it?
Is it difficult learning
how to play the violin?
It's not too bad.
Why do you ask?
When I surveyed the
mission site earlier today...
Yeah...
I met this boy. His
name was Emilio.
He's a bellhop who works
at our mark's hotel...
Really?
I think he mistook
my weapon case
for some kind of
violin case...
And he asked me to
play for him sometime.
I can only play some practice
things like scales and stuff.
I don't think
I'd be much help.
Oh, that's okay.
Anyway...
It would probably be pretty
hard for you to see him again.
Sure... You
have a point.
Then again... Maybe he
fell in love with you
and wonders if he'll ever
get to see you again.
I wouldn't know how to figure
out anything like that...
But if anyone ever felt
like that about me,
especially if it was
Emilio, it'd make me happy.
Rico, if you wanna try my
violin... I'll show you how.
Really?
Sure.
Your turn.
There you go. Now relax
your right hand a bit.
Isn't that sound
just the loveliest?
Lobby
surveillance here...
Is the hotel...
delivering room service now?
Are his bodyguards
with him?
[Hilshire] No, just
he and his secretary,
asking for
room service.
How is our bug
working in there?
The room is loud
and clear, boss.
He said he was getting
ready to take a shower...
Should we wait?
Yes... We'll time
out until he's in.
[Jean] Henrietta and Triela,
you two remain on standby.
I want us to have as little
visibility as possible.
Room service here.
It's finished.
[Jean] Return immediately.
I'm sending in the cleaners.
I'm leaving right now.
Jean, we have a
hotel employee.
He just walked
onto the third floor.
[Jean] Rico. Rico,
do you read me?
Hi, Rico.
What are you doing here?
And why are you wearing a hotel
uniform...? I don't get it.
I can't... I can't
remember what to say.
What do I say at
a time like this?
Rico...
What are those words
I'm looking for?
Of course...
I remember.
I am sorry.
Every morning when I wake up,
my first thought
is always a worry.
I worry if my body
will still be here.
And it's always
wonderful discovering
that my body
still works.
Nothing could ever be
the same kind of relief.
One day I'm locked
in my own head,
and now I have a body
to move however I want.
At the Social
Welfare Agency...
I really like my life here.
I can finally be myself.