[Jean] Good to see you
again Captain Raballo.
Jean... What could
you possibly want
with an old
retiree like me?
Well, recently I got
a new job...
And we're looking
for good instructors.
You know after you
left the unit...
I heard some
interesting things.
Can I assume you're involved
with that shady organization?
It's a line of work that
both us are well suited for.
You mean, revenge at all
costs. Isn't that how it goes?
Wouldn't you like to return
to the Military Police?
After all, that
job was your life.
We could arrange for
your re-enlistment.
[Raballo] So is she
one of them?
Not yet.
That is up to you.
Captain...?
Is she the one
you'll choose?
She wears glasses.
That's not a problem.
Eyesight is part of our
correction procedures as well.
When you make your
final decision,
we'll hand her over in
tip-top combat form.
You speak as if... the
agency can do anything.
Yes... If it means you
will join our fight,
then we can...
So, will you choose her?
[Raballo] I guess
she's as good as any.
[Jean]
Great.
I think you made
the right choice.
Now your first job as her
Handler is to give her a name.
Wait, do I have to
give her a girl's name?
No, it doesn't need
to be a girl's name...
You're free to name her
whatever you'd like.
I suppose that would make
the job more impersonal.
[Jean] Do whatever you
need to feel comfortable.
It's about
time you hit one.
Don't bother
leaving this range
until you can consistently hit
that target from 20 yards.
I'm heading back.
Keep shooting, Claes.
Captain Raballo.
Yeah?
I have yet to see Claes
around the grounds today.
Me neither.
Her gunplay needs work
so I told her to keep
practicing yesterday.
I haven't
seen her since.
[Jean] What do
you mean?
I haven't seen her means
I haven't seen her.
She didn't even bother
giving me a final report.
I see.
It takes time for our
girls to grow accustomed
to their new implants.
Some longer than others...
Remember how long it took
you to learn to walk again
after your new leg.
You have be
patient with them.
Learning to move freely should
come before firearms training.
A musical instrument
may help out.
Or even writing in
longhand may be effective.
I don't remember any of this
being in my job description.
[Jean] Check the
shooting range.
I'll bet you
she's still there.
What is she...?
[Jean] Because you
ordered her to be there.
Hello Claes.
Raballo...
I'm sorry sir... I still can't
hit the target every time.
Idiot... How can you expect
to get better at anything
when you're outside in
the rain all night?
Let's go.
Okay, Claes... We gotta change
up your training somehow.
Come in.
[Claes]
Raballo?
What is
it, Claes?
Did you sneak
out of your room?
Jean woke me up. He said I
needed to come talk to you.
He did...? He didn't tell
me... Well, have a seat.
You sure do
have a lot...
A lot of what?
Books.
Wait until the rest of
my stuff arrives.
You're looking at only
half my collection.
Filling these bookcases
will be quite the chore.
I'll help you fill
them if you want.
You should mind
your own business.
Yes, sir.
We may not look it on
the outside, but...
people like us,
in our profession
tend to read
books all the time.
I've found that uneducated
people make poor soldiers.
What kind of
books do you read?
Well, let's
take a look.
Right now I'm reading a book
on how to grow vegetables.
I believe it doesn't matter
what subjects you read,
it's the act of exercising
your mind that counts.
What kind of
books do you read?
They gave me a few textbooks,
but I haven't opened them yet.
I'll read everything
I can get my hands on...
If that's what it takes
to make a good soldier.
That's good.
I'm suspending your firearms
practice for a while.
We're going out
tomorrow morning.
[Claes] It's
not a holiday.
You sure
it's okay?
Yes.
I consider this
training as well...
I put the bait
on for you.
Now just cast the line
underhanded like I showed you.
All right.
So what do I do now?
Now, you just sit and
wait for the fish.
Are you bored?
Huh?
I used to
always get bored
whenever I went fishing
with my old man.
At the time though...
I didn't understand
the joys of just sitting
and watching the
day pass you by.
I'm not bored. I'm
actually enjoying this.
You know this is so
different than anything
else I've
experienced so far...
I think I like
being a fisherman.
Understand that I
don't care about you...
All you are to me is
a job, nothing more.
The only thing
I care about...
Is returning to
the Military Police.
Mind if I ask you
about your leg?
A pistol accidentally
discharged into my leg
during my MP days.
Three years at the agency
and they'll get me back in.
That was Jean's
promise to me.
If that's the case,
you can count on me to act as
your legs from now on, sir.
Knock it off!
Did you not hear what I
just got finished saying?
Look! You've got a
bite! Pull it in!
[Claes] We visited countless
other lakes after that day...
Lombardy, Veneto, and
Piemonte, just to name a few.
At the agency, we
rarely ever talked.
We got our work done and
stayed true to our roles
as teacher and student,
but for some reason,
we would always talk at the
lake as if we were family.
It was our own
unspoken rule.
[Raballo] Alright... That was
the last train for the night...
Now Claes.
We're gonna do a little on the
job training this evening.
So only take them out
if it's in self-defense.
If you can't handle
these subway punks,
then you can forget
about the real thing.
This should be a walk in
the park for you, Claes.
I'll do my best.
Alfonso... Claes
has made contact...
Keep the police off
our backs for a while.
[Alfonso]
Roger that.
Raballo.
Alfonso. Bring the garbage
truck around to our position.
[Claes]
I'm sorry.
You... idiot.
Knowing when to
shoot your weapon
is more important than
shooting itself... Dammit.
Don't you
understand...?
It's too late once you're
within a knife's range.
Next time don't
hesitate to shoot.
Yes.
Jose... You need to teach your
girl a little consistency.
Easier said than done...
So I should increase
her conditioning?
No Jose. That's
not what I meant.
You trying to
kill yourself?!
Raballo! Stop it!
Shut up!
What's she doing here
if she can't even
handle a gun correctly?
Did you assume it
wouldn't jam...
just because it's
a modern gun?
This blasé attitude is only
going to get someone killed
Raballo! Behind you!
Henrietta!
Stand down!
Captain...
You're not at fault.
It seems to me that Jose isn't
fully devoted to her training.
But the problem lies within
their brainwashing procedures.
I now see that the system
could use some improvement.
Do you feel it necessary
to recondition these girls?
I have no doubt Jose
will object to it, but...
both of these girls would
benefit from the brainwashing
for safety
purposes alone.
But if you went
through with that,
you'd be decreasing
their life span.
It may seem tragic to you, but
it comes with the territory.
Besides, this doesn't
concern you anyway.
Once the agency
lays the groundwork,
you'll be back with
the Military Police.
In the meantime,
take some R&amp;R for yourself
while she's recovering.
Jose.
I'm sorry for what happened,
Raballo. It was all my fault.
I just spoke with Jean.
You're not gonna allow her
to be reconditioned
again, are you?
[Jose] Of course not. I'm
gonna fight it all the way.
I see.
I can't figure out a way
to help them distinguish
between
friend and foe
without redoing the
conditioning process...
Fighting violence with
violence is all I know.
It's what my entire
career is based on.
[Raballo] 'Good soldiers read
books' Huh? What a load...
Don't tell Jean
I was, uh...
complaining like
this, you know.
[Agent B] So, what's
with the MP captain?
[Alfonso] He doesn't know
what to do with himself
and this
free time.
[Agent C] I think he
might have reached
his breaking point already.
No surprises there...
considering the
business we're in.
[Agent B] No need to
force him into continuing.
[Claes]
Raballo!
Hello, Claes.
It's been awhile...
Did you check
out today?
I managed to get out
of there a day early...
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
I heard a rumor that you're
quitting the agency...
Henrietta told
me all about it
when she came to
visit me the other day.
Oh, so you and
Henrietta made up?
What?
Nothing...
Don't worry about me...
I'm just gonna
relax here
until you're officially
released tomorrow...
I may go fishing, or finish
reading a book I started.
[Raballo] I don't know...
Oh, I almost forgot.
I have some things I
wanted to give you...
First, my room key.
From now on, you can read my
books whenever you want.
There should be more than
enough for you to enjoy.
Also, I wanted you to have
your old glasses back.
Why'd you
keep these?
I've tried to turn you
into a one man army,
a killing
machine...
but lately, I've felt
guilty as hell doing it.
Always remember
to think clearly
before pulling the trigger...
No matter what the agency
orders you to do...
you mustn't use your killing
abilities outside of work.
I want you to be
the gentle Claes
whenever you put
those glasses on.
Now don't think of
this as an order...
It's a heart to heart promise.
Understand?
I do.
Hello?
Roberto Dandini.
Hey there- Good to
hear from you.
Yes, we looked into
your proposal...
Just me and the
editor know about it...
Yeah, we're game.
I've been
watching my back
and no one has followed me
for the past four days...
Now I expect absolute
secrecy on your end.
You sound paranoid... No,
don't even worry about that.
It's all taken
care of... So then.
What's your big story?
Today?
Like right now?
Where do you want to
meet? Okay. Got it.
Raballo sure is
taking his time.
Yeah.
Hi, Claes.
[Claes] Jean?
Captain Raballo...
...is dead.
He was in a
hit-and-run accident
two days ago
outside of Rome.
He died instantly.
[Triela] Jean!
You can't just come out
and tell her like that!
[Jean] You shut
your mouth.
[Triela]
Claes! Say something!
Take her.
Claes!!
[Jean] Unfortunately, this
girl is no longer of use to us.
An established Handler is
always difficult to replace.
[Doctor A]
I have a proposal.
Yes?
There is something...
We've been looking
forward to this testing
for quite some time...
If Claes would
be kind enough...
...to assist us.
Preparations complete.
See you...
I'll be back soon.
Bye.
Have fun.
I don't participate in
operations like everyone else.
In fact, I'm not even allowed
to step outside the agency.
For as long as
my memory allows,
this is the only way
of life I've known.
Go ahead and
change clothes.
You can put your
things over there.
[Doctor A]
Claes, Are you ready?
I want to test
your shoulder joints,
so pull as
hard as you can.
Okay.
Alright.
Let's begin.
How's her muscle
output looking?
Abdominal and tricep
muscles still not at maximum.
Now Claes... I said to
pull as hard as you can.
Give it some more
effort! Harder!
Harder! Harder!
I need more!
Her right shoulder
joint just gave out.
Hey, Claes.
Take a break.
We'll give you
painkillers in a moment...
Send her out for repairs.
Right.
Compare next week's muscle
model with today's data.
As I continue this
testing day after day,
something always
comes to mind.
[Claes] Shall we?
Huh?
So what are
we doing today?
We are going to plant
a vegetable garden.
Jean actually gave me
permission when I asked him.
Why a
vegetable garden?
I'm not really sure. It
just seemed like a good idea.
Claes.
Huh?
Don't you ever get lonely?
What do you mean?
Just you always having to stay
at the agency by yourself...
I'm pretty sure I
would die of loneliness
if I didn't
have Jose here.
You know what Henrietta?
Huh?
If I'm lonely one evening,
I'll decide that for myself.
Cooking food, drawing
pictures and playing music
is all fun, and I have as
many books to read as I want.
But of all the things I enjoy
the most, it's the idle time.
Just sitting outside
and watching the day
pass into night.
I think my father taught
me that a long time ago,
or was it someone else?
I get that feeling a lot.