So, eighty-six
the cop, too?
Yes. It's a
perfect opportunity.
Nobody knows
you're here.
But don't get careless
out there, okay?
Be sure and get photos
when the job's done.
Got it.
Lauro, this is Elsa.
Right, what's
the set-up?
The same as
yesterday...
There's one guard positioned
outside the front door.
Okay, take them out, all
of them. And Elsa...
Yes, sir.
Don't forget the photos.
You know, as chief
of police...
You really should
start thinking about
who you'd rather
be working with,
the government or
the terrorists.
If you keep getting
in our way,
I won't hesitate
to eliminate you.
You see, we have a
job to do as well.
Lauro.
Are you
finished?
Yes, sir. Everything inside
went just as you planned.
You got
the photos?
Oh, yes.
There's still one exposure
left... Next time,
shoot the
whole roll.
There.
Get it developed as
soon as we get back.
Yes, sir.
Alright, let's
get outta here.
Zweihundert,
zwanzig, drei...
Euro?
Oiro--
In German "e-u"
sounds like oy.
Oh.
And, remember, you always
read from the last digit,
so twenty-three would
be "drei und zwanzig".
You really need to
study the numbers more.
Five point five six is
"fuenf komma juenf sechs"
and seven point six two is
"sieben komma sechs zwei".
Elsa?
Are you understanding
all of this okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Well-
Kids are just
like adults,
get them together in a big room
and not everybody gets along.
It's the same with us
"conditioned" girls.
Elsa has a room
to herself
and doesn't have much to
do with the rest of us.
Of course, it's not like we
try to make her feel welcome.
I've never even
spoke to her.
Triela, you talk
with Elsa, don't you?
No, not really. I suppose
not any more than I have to.
I'm...
...not good
at talking.
Why bother? Elsa only
cares about Lauro.
Actually, to be honest with
you, Henrietta... I hate her.
You hate her but you
still try to help her?
Oh, I don't know...
I think it's just too
easy to ignore people
you don't really
like, you know?
I guess I like
the challenge.
And you know, speaking of
people I don't like...
You and Claes used to
be just like Elsa
when you first came
to the agency.
So, you helped us
change, Triela?
I wouldn't give
myself all the credit.
It also depends on the
Handler and the conditioning.
What do you mean?
The Handler?
So, you get along fine with
Claes but not with Elsa?
You realize Claes is
pretty unsociable too.
Yeah...
I don't know.
Claes is just
different somehow.
So, you think I'm
unsociable... huh, Triela?
Here...
Dessert today is a Ricotta
Tart... they're pretty good.
Thank you,
Madame Claes.
You're welcome, and
don't call me Madame.
Marco.
Hey, Jose.
A little
target practice?
Sure, why not?
How's Angelica doing?
Oh... I'm getting
better everyday!
That's good.
Just don't push
yourself too hard.
I won't.
Henrietta, you should be a
sharper shot than me by now.
I know. But I just can't
seem to get any better.
You have to understand there
aren't any big secrets to it.
The only way you can
improve is with dedication
and constant
practice.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Jose!
Lauro--
I thought you were in
Tuscany hunting the R.F..
The primary
mission's completed.
But the local cops have
become a problem...
...hiding terrorists, so,
we'll have to deal with them.
I see.
So, I saw that you're
off duty this week
and I need you're help,
if you can swing it.
Let's meet up and
we can discuss it.
Sounds good.
Well, gotta run.
Am I going to
work with Elsa?
Maybe.
We'll see.
Let's go.
Okay.
Who's there?
What do
you want?
I thought... I thought
that maybe we could talk.
So, the local
police chief
is on the take and
harboring terrorists.
I killed one of his
Captains last week
to send him
a message...
But, he's still
holding out.
And yesterday, he actually
threatened to go public
with everything he
knows about the Agency.
Our superiors have finally
authorized his elimination.
The Chief of Police, huh? So
what kind of plan you got?
Everything's
worked out.
It's actually going to
be very simple.
The church towers around
the police station
are perfect
for sniping.
With two shooters,
it's a piece of cake.
That's the plan?
Yeah, why? Is Henrietta
a bad shot or something?
No... she's an
accurate shot.
It's just... Well, I kinda
wonder if she'll be in top form
in front of people she's
not used to working with.
We'll do it.
If nothing else,
this will help boost
Henrietta's confidence.
Hey, Jose?
Tell me... Do you always worry
about the cyborgs like that?
Yeah.
So, I guess all the rumors
I've heard are true.
What rumors are those?
Oh, you know...
Yeah, I know. You believe
everything you hear?
Here.
Listen, I've seen the
way you treat your cyborg.
I just can't stand guys
who let themselves
get too attached.
Well then... Why did you invite
one them out for drinks?
Because...
I hate guys
like you.
But I am
curious...
curious as to what makes
someone like you tick.
It's easier to figure
out what's going on
in someone's head
after they've had
a few drinks.
Then I can decide if the person
has any redeemable qualities.
I believe everyone is of value
somehow, even if you hate them.
Even if I don't
think like you,
you seem like an
okay guy, Jose.
Well, at least
there's that.
It's like Kennedy
once said...
Let us not be blind to
our differences. Okay?
We have nothing
to talk about.
But... it sounds like
we might be working
together
someday soon.
Well, then I'll
warn you now--
If you even think about
getting in Lauro's way...
you'll regret it.
Elsa?
Why do you push
us all away?
Tell me, who's more
important to you,
your Handler or
the other cyborgs?
My handler's the most
important thing to me.
Nothing else
matters. Nothing.
Everything I do... is for
the sake of our fratello.
When Lauro's gone and I'm left
here alone, I think about him.
What he's
doing...
Even though I know tomorrow may
be the last day of our lives.
Don't talk to
me about us!
We have our handlers
and that's it!
That's not...
You know that's
not true!
I like Jose, I
like him a lot...
But there's got to be more
for us than just that!
Well...
I don't think there's
anything left to talk about.
Would you
just leave?
So, Lauro?
Yeah, what?
Obviously, it's
important to you
to get along with
your colleagues,
or we wouldn't
be here.
Yeah, it is.
I think it's good
that guys like us
can get together
and hang out.
But, don't you think you're
pretty hard on Elsa?
Look, Jose... Don't confuse
cyborgs for colleagues.
You'll never see
me getting hung up
on those things
like you are.
I just don't think
of them like that.
I mean, they're
definitely cool.
They can clean your
guns for you...
They'll even bring you
lunch if you tell them to.
But, that's as far
as it goes for me.
To be honest,
though,
if it weren't for the
cyborgs in Section Two...
I wouldn't even
have a job.
Ahh! Listen to me rambling
on like I know everything...
You do your thing,
I'll do mine.
I'm curious, Lauro.
Huh?
Why did you join
the agency?
Well, the pay
isn't too bad.
But, I can't keep
doing this forever.
I guess the cyborgs
have it pretty tough...
but then so do
us handlers.
Yeah, we don't have anybody
around to take care of us.
Cheers to that.
You ready, Jose?
We're set.
I took the liberty of sending
the heavy stuff ahead.
You're smarter
than I thought.
Well, I have
done this before.
Henrietta.
Yes?
Is this your first
time here in Tuscany?
Yes, it is.
When we finish with
the job tomorrow,
I thought we might take
a little look around town.
Does a vacation
sound good to you?
Yeah!
Lauro?
Hmm?
I want you to
know... that I'll...
I'll do
my best.
Oh, well...
that's good.
If we shoot the
police chief
right in front of
his headquarters...
It'll send a clear message
to the other small town cops.
How'd you manage to score
such a perfect location?
You know, I have
my connections.
These old churches
and museums
are all under
government control.
Lauro?
What should I do
with the Hecate?
Get it ready next
to your SIG for now.
But, I don't want to use
it unless we have to.
Right.
Lauro... Is Elsa
doing all right today?
Huh?
I don't know... She
seems fine to me.
No... She... she
seems a little uneasy.
Sometimes they get careless
when they're like that.
I wouldn't
worry about it.
Elsa's never let
me down before.
She's been well trained.
I think maybe you're
a little too sensitive
for your own good, man.
Maybe...
Okay...
Everyone ready? The chief
should be in the second car.
Wait until you see him on
the steps before you shoot.
The timing has
to be perfect.
Have you been practicing
your sharp-shooting?
Yes, Jose.
Elsa!
Pay attention!
Yes!
Elsa, the safety's still on!
I'm sorry!
Alright... Jose, switch with
Elsa. She's not concentrating.
Got it.
No, Lauro!
I'm fine.
I can do it!
Sorry, Elsa.
Hurry, he's getting
out of the car!
Wait...
Perfect, good work.
Let's get out of here!
Elsa! Let's go!
Useless...
Henrietta!
Yes!