What do you think?
What if Jose's mad at me?
I heard you put on
quite a show in Sicily.
Maybe I over
did it a little.
Yeah, do
you think?
I just hope he's
not mad at me.
I wouldn't worry. When I saw
him, he seemed pretty normal.
Really?
Mm hmm.
I hope you're right.
Henrietta, Triela, move out.
Good job guys.
Stay
focused.
Yes sir.
See what I mean?
Uh-huh.
Next team- Angelica,
Rico, move out.
Okay!
Angelica!
Are you okay?
Angelica's gone down!
Shut the program down.
You okay?
I'm gonna
be fine.
Marco... I'm sorry...
See, I'm okay now.
Not when you're limping
around like that, you're not.
Have Ferro take you
back to the infirmary.
Yes, sir.
Maybe you should
have waited
before getting her
back into training.
You're responsible
for being aware
of Angelica's limitations.
Look, she practically begged
me to let her do it, so I did.
Back to the
training room!
Yes, sir!
First the problem with Elsa,
and now Angelica's injury.
Seems we've had
some setbacks.
It's just like
we expected.
We'll have setbacks
and progress-
it's all part of the process.
Come now, why don't you
just level with us?
Section 2 is
not working out.
You should just be honest
about it and admit it.
That's only
your opinion.
Overall, I think
there's still a lot
of potential
in Section 2.
Let's try giving
it some more time.
Be honest, Chief...
What's wrong?
It's not going
quite as we planned.
You see... they're
still very much human.
You're going to have to
start making progress soon.
I can't keep putting
them off forever.
Yes, I know.
According to our source
within the Republican Faction,
they're planning to kidnap
Senator Viste's daughter.
What
source?
Fillipo Adani-
He handles the cash for
their operations. He's solid.
Adani says they're going
to grab Caterina Viste.
Fortunately, she's matches up
with one of Section Two's girls
in age and appearance.
They'll kidnap
one of our cyborgs
in place of the
Senator's daughter.
Then we take 'em down.
A cyborg as a decoy?
That's risky.
Yeah, he's right, I
don't know about this...
This is what Section Two's
for, or course it's risky!
But, what if we...
Section Two's under a
microscope right now...
We're going to have to push the
envelope if we want to survive.
We'll use Claes
as the decoy.
They're saying our next mission
is going to be a big one.
Oh, yeah... And
according to Hillshire
it's going to be
dangerous, too.
Are you scared, Claes?
To be used as a decoy?
Not really-
Is it that grain
of wheat thing?
Not at all, I'm just
doing what I'm told.
Wheat...?
What wheat?
A grain of wheat must
fall to the ground
before it can
do any good.
New life springs
from fallen grains.
The moral is that nothing good
happens without some sacrifice.
Marco.
Oh, won't you please let me
take part in the mission!
This is for real... I cannot
tolerate another failure.
I'll do my very best Marco,
I promise... Please, let me!
I'll think about it.
Thank you...
Jean, the car is on
its way downtown.
Copy that.
Ready?
Let's go.
We've got the
transmitter's signal...
The car's heading
north now...
Away from
downtown.
Were there any problems
tracking the vehicle?
We placed a tracking beacon
in one of Claes' teeth
before we sent her out.
And we also scattered
Section 2 lookouts
on all the major roads
into and out of Rome.
But the vehicle headed into
the mountains north of town
and we lost the signal.
The terrorists have already
contacted the Senator
at his home.
We're holding their
comrades in a local prison.
They want them released.
At least we know they
haven't figured out
she's not the real girl.
And if they do find
out she's a decoy-
Claes- she hardly any
combat experience.
If they find out she's a
decoy, they will kill her.
The whole thing's
a big mess...
Chief-
I'm calling a friend
in the military.
For backup.
I knew we could
strike a deal.
Would you mind if I spoke
with her alone for a moment?
Alright, make it
quick, okay-
Hi there. What are
you doing, studying?
No... it's just
a book on plants.
Reading about
plants, huh?
You know, the plant
life in the north
is totally different
than the south.
Yes... Evergreens are more
common in the mountains
where the altitude is higher.
So, aren't you afraid?
Not really... Besides, I find
reading to be therapeutic.
I've always liked reading,
ever since I was a little girl.
And, besides...
Someone like me could
never be a grain of wheat.
Well-
Good luck.
Thanks! See you later.
That's odd... They don't care
if the girl sees their faces.
Yeah, they must be
planning to kill her...
What a bunch of idiots,
if they only knew who
they were holding.
I tell ya, I hope that kid
teaches them a good lesson.
A grain of
wheat, huh...?
What did you say?
Forget about it, let's
just get out of here.
Hey, Chief!
The city police just
received an anonymous call.
What?
They're at a villa up
north, in the mountains.
There's even a sketch
of the villa's layout.
How reliable is
this information?
The R.F. could have
leaked this stuff
just to throw
off the police.
Apparently the anonymous
caller was a woman.
A woman?
Well, it looks like
that's the info we got.
We can send a team
out to recon the area
but that'll take time,
which we don't have.
And, the whole mission will
fail if we hesitate any longer.
I know it's a
risky proposition
however we have no
choice but to move in
and take down
the villa.
Okay, we're going to
approach the target location
from the mountains on
the southeast side.
We'll move out in teams- Jose
and Henrietta, Jean and Rico.
You two teams will engage
the front entrance
and draw as much fire
from the terrorists
as you can
that direction.
My team will enter
from the terrace.
Hold up!
Good luck...
All right,
understood.
The army recon team
has reacquired
Claes'
transmitter signal.
Looks like this
was the right move.
But the show's
not over yet.
It's vital that Section 2
take the whole terrorist cell.
Angelica--
It's okay just
remain calm.
Get up here!
We're in position-
what's you status?
We're on the roof now,
moving into position.
We'll move out
in three minutes.
Synchronize
your watch.
Five, four, three,
two, one, mark!
Rico, you cover
us from here.
Got it.
All right...
let's go.
'kay
What the hell
is this?
What the...?
The cops?
Nope.
All the guards are dead!
We're under attack!
Angelica!
Where are you going?!
Triela, what's up?
Angelica took
off upstairs!
Don't move!
You brought this
all on yourself.
Angelica!
Claes...
Are you okay?
Angelica's been hit!
Angelica?
Sorry
Marco...
You screwed
up bad.
What the hell were you
trying to do in there?
Trying to get
us all killed?!
Ugh... you're
freakin useless!
Marco, ease up!
How you feeling,
Angelica?
Fine.
Well, you sure seem
to be doing better.
Soon you'll be
walking around
and you'll get to come
back to the dorm.
I think you all
know the truth.
What?
We're all
going to die!
We'll all die empty and
alone! It's the truth!
Marco's so angry at me
that I wish I could die now
and get it over with...
Why can't I just die?!
If you want to die
then kill yourself!
I should never have
bothered saving you!
Claes?!
I couldn't see her eyes well
enough from behind her glasses
to tell if she was
crying or just angry.
But I wish
I could have.
I know that what
Angelica said...
We're all
going to die...
Echoed true in
Claes' mind
just like they did
for the rest of us.