[HAKASE]
Nano!
Nano? Hey, Nano!
[NANO]
What is it?
[HAKASE]
Are you outside?
Yes.
[HAKASE]
Nano?
[NANO]
Yeah?
Hey, Nano!
[NANO]
Huh?
[HAKASE]
Looky, look!
I'm a cat, check me-owt!
Meow!
Sakamoto! I'm like you!
I'm a cat, check me-owt!
[SAKAMOTO gasping]
Check me-owt! See?
[NANO]
Hakase.
I think your cat look
is purr-fect!
--[HAKASE] Meow?
--[SAKAMOTO] Hm?
Meow! Checking me-owt?
[NANO]
That's paw-some!
Here and meow?
[NANO]
So a-mew-sing!
[HAKASE]
You're checking me-owt!
[NANO]
I'm really feline it!
[HAKASE]
Meow I'm a cat!
[NANO]
You're kitten me!
[HAKASE]
I'm fur-real!
[NANO] Meow you're talkin'!
[HAKASE]
Meow and fur-ever!
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome household.
[NAKANOJOU]
Why is the Earth round?
How do planes and rockets fly?
Why do magnets attract
and repel one another?
Every one of those questions
can be answered by science.
Our society is infatuated
by the afterlife.
Things like ghosts, and
paranormal phenomena.
But such stupid stuff
couldn't possibly be real!
They can't exist.
There's no way.
[NAKANOJOU]
Which is why...
...I refuse to believe
in psychic mediums!
[NAKANOJOU]
During one of my days off,
I decided to make an eight-hour
trek up Mount Osore.
And the closer I
got to the summit,
the faster my heart raced.
Was there really
a medium up here?
If there was, then where?
What was the point of living
in such a secluded place?
Maybe if...
[gasps]
[NAKANOJOU]
I found one!
All right, good.
I'll say there's a spirit
I need channeled.
[NAKANOJOU]
Excuse me.
Yes?
[NAKANOJOU]
Um.
Can you to channel
the spirit of Soap?
Yeah, sure.
Hello! It's me, Soap!
[NAKANOJOU gasping]
[MEDIUM A]
Brr, ow! Mic test. Check.
Check, one, two. Check, check.
Testing. One, two, three.
[NAKANOJOU]
What the--?
It feels like something
crazy is going on here.
Could there actually be somebody
out there with the name Soap?
Testing. Check. One, two.
Yes, it's me. I'm Soap.
Yup, yup, yup, this is Soap.
[NAKANOJOU]
No. I can't falter now.
If I just keep asking her stuff,
I'm sure she'll end up
contradicting herself somehow.
I have a question.
If you're really Soap, then
what's your blood type, huh?
Dunno.
[NAKANOJOU] Let's try again with
someone more recognizable.
[NAKANOJOU]
Excuse me.
Could you channel the spirit
of the great Oda Nobunaga?
Give me a break here, would ya?
[screams]
[NAKANOJOU] She's refusing my
request without even trying?
Wait. I'm dealing with
an elderly woman here.
She might be
overexerting herself.
I'll figure out another angle.
[NAKANOJOU screams]
[NAKANOJOU exhales]
[NAKANOJOU]
Thank you for your time.
I'm gonna go home.
I don't like criticizing people.
Realizing that alone
makes this trip worth it.
Oh, one more thing.
[NAKANOJOU]
Uh?
[MEDIUM A]
That'll be 5,000 yen.
[YUUKO]
Huh...
[YUUKO grunts]
[YUUKO screaming]
[gasps]
[STUDENTS laughing]
[BOTH]
Oh?
--[KOUJIROU] Mm. Ah--
--[MISATO gasps]
[WEBOSHII screams]
Ah-chee.
[MISATO]
Wha--?
[MIO]
Boys are so weird.
[YUUKO]
Okay, you ready?
Rock, paper, scissors!
[YUUKO groans]
[YUUKO]
Huh? Wait, what? Huh?
Come on, Mai! Wake up!
You're supposed to bop me
on the head when you win!
Didn't I just explain the rules?
You're no fun.
That hurts, you know?
It hurts more than
actually getting smacked.
All right. Let's try this
again one more time.
If you lose, you guard,
and if you win, you get to hit.
[YUUKO]
Wah!
I didn't mean hit me
right this second!
Why would you do that?
Because I won the game earlier.
That was earlier!
You can't do it now!
Act when the time is right!
Live in the moment!
Strike when the iron is hot!
Just be spontaneous or whatever!
[BOTH] ♪ First comes a rock,
what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors
and a one, two, three! ♪
[HAKASE]
You're Nya-no now!
[YUUKO]
Whatever, let's try it again.
Fresh start, okay?
Rock, paper, scissors!
[YUUKO]
She doesn't even care at all!
Do you enjoy making me
look like a fool?
[YUUKO]
She's so not in the mood.
And now I'm not either.
Uh, where do you think
you're going?
There it is.
[YUUKO] That statue.
Where did... you get that?
Carved it.
[YUUKO]
Oh, thank goodness.
Here I thought it got
reincarnated or something!
[MAI]
I'll put this right here.
[YUUKO]
She looks strangely happy.
Hey, let's forget about that
silly statue and keep playing.
Kay. Rock, paper, scissors!
Uh. I don't think that counts.
Okay, maybe it does!
[YUUKO]
Unbelievable. She's so vicious.
[YUUKO whimpers]
[YUUKO] I'm begging you,
Mai! Please cut it out!
Just play by the rules! And no
using that statue as a weapon!
Are you ready now?
First comes a rock.
One, two, three.
Uh.
[gasps]
You did it right.
That's it!
You just played the game!
Aw! I knew you could
do it all along!
Cool! Let's go for
another round!
Ready? And first comes a...
...rock.
God is dead!
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
God is indeed dead.
[YUUKO sniffles]
What gives?
Why'd you hit me?
We haven't even played
the next round yet!
[MAI]
Maybe it's because
I don't really feel
like playing.
[YUUKO]
Oh.
[YUUKO] Then can I see your
statue thing? Please?
[MAI]
Yeah, sure.
[NANO] I'm headed to the library
to return some books!
Take care of the house
while I'm gone!
[HAKASE]
'Kay!
Huh?
Why does Nano's daruma guy
only have one eyeball filled in?
I know! If I help her out and
fix the other eye for her,
I bet she'll really
appreciate it!
She'll be so grateful, she
might even say that I can eat
all the snacks I want,
whenever I want!
[HAKASE laughs]
[HAKASE]
Oh... I think I messed it up,
'cause that doesn't look
right. Now what do I do?
Nano'll get mad, and...
Uh! What if she gets so mad
she takes my snacks away?!
No more snacks for
Hakase ever again!
[HAKASE whimpers]
[HAKASE] Just put a little this,
and a little there, and uh...
[HAKASE whines]
[SAKAMOTO]
Is something wrong?
Uh! I don't know what
to do Sakamoto! Look.
[SAKAMOTO]
At what? Whoa!
What happened to its face?
You did a number on that thing.
I was just trying to
even out the eyes.
[SAKAMOTO]
Hmm...
[SAKAMOTO] Don't you worry.
I know what we have to do.
[BOTH laughing]
[NANO]
I'm home!
[BOTH]
Gah!
[SAKAMOTO]
You're on your own.
[HAKASE]
Sakamoto!
[NANO] Where are you
off to in such a hurry?
Hey, Hakase!
Sorry I took so long,
but I was picking out
new books to bring home.
What'd you do while I was gone?
Wait, what the--?!
What's going on with your belly?
Well, uh. You know how
it goes sometimes.
[NANO]
What does that even mean?
[gasps] It's coming!
[NANO gasping]
Wait.
There's no way. You can't
possibly be having a child.
I'm having one now!
The baby is coming!
O... kay? Are you pulling
some sort of prank?
I'm not! I'm bringing your
baby brother into the world!
[squeaks]
[NANO gasping]
[NANO laughs]
It's your baby brother.
Goo-goo. Ga-ga.
[SAKAMOTO]
This could be a problem.
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
[YUUKO]
Mio! You wanna play a game?
[MIO]
What kind?
How 'bout we play Kokkuri?
[MIO]
What's that?
Wait. You've never
heard of it before?
Nope, never.
[YUUKO] Okay then, I'm gonna
break it down for you.
You start by drawing
a shrine gate
at the top of the paper here.
Then you write Yes and No on the
sides, and the alphabet below.
[MIO]
Okay.
And in some regions, I think
you're supposed to draw
a little piece of fried
tofu somewhere
on the paper too, but...
Let's stick to the simplified
version for now.
Then. You have to
make sure to open up
a north facing entrance
so the spirits can get inside.
Next, we take a ten-yen coin
and set it on top of the gate
we drew at the beginning.
Finally, we both touch
the coin with our fingers
and ask it a question.
There's no restriction on what
kind of things you can ask
the spirit, so the sky's
basically the limit here.
[MIO]
Sure.
And then, without
any effort of our own,
spirits will slide the coin
around and spell out
the answers to our
questions for us.
Really?
Yeah! I know it's awesome,
but some things are taboo.
First off, you can't play
the game by yourself
and you can't half-ass it.
Because if you do,
you might get possessed!
[MIO]
Oh?
You also risk getting possessed
if you stop partway through,
so you gotta commit.
Right, I get it.
Now you know how to play
the wonderfully spooky game
of Kokkuri! So, whaddaya
say we give it a shot?
[MIO]
Nah, I'm good.
[YUUKO]
Ahhhh....
[NAKANOJOU grunts]
[NAKANOJOU panting]
[IZUMI] So, uh, that
concludes the lessons
I have for you today.
Remember that we'll be
having a quiz tomorrow,
so make sure you don't
forget to study tonight!
[CHIYODA] What? Can't you
push the quiz back?
It doesn't matter
if you take it later,
you're still gonna bomb it.
[STUDENTS laugh]
[CHIYODA]
Yeah, probably.
[YUUKO]
Excuse me, Miss Sakurai?
How can I help you, Miss Aioi?
I just had a question
for you, if you don't mind.
Go ahead!
Well, about that English test
we had a little while ago.
What is this supposed to be?
[IZUMI] The correct answer
for that one was "Fly."
[YUUKO] No, I'm not
asking about the answer.
I'm wondering if you were
the one who drew this
low-level looking monster.
Yes, I did. I figured it
would help make the test
a little easier if there
was a visual aid.
[YUUKO] Well then, you have some
pretty awesome drawings!
How kind of you.
But my drawings aren't great,
so I'm sorry if they were
hard to identify.
[YUUKO]
Uhh...
[YUUKO gasps]
I know!
How about I give you a hand,
and draw you a picture that you
can put on the next exam!
I promise it'll be
something really cool!
Sure, okay!
[YUUKO]
Oh! Hey, Mio!
[MIO]
Hm?
Check it out! My drawing is
gonna be in the next test!
[MIO]
Really? Why?
[YUUKO] The teacher
said she would use it!
I bet you could get
yours on there too
if you drew a little doodle
of your own right now.
Yeah, I dunno if I'm cut out
for something like that.
Huh. What do mean?
[MIO]
I'm just not the greatest.
And besides, I gotta
go return this thing.
[YUUKO]
If you say so! 'Kay!
I think I'm gonna draw
a cool-looking dude!
[MIO gasps]
[YUUKO humming]
[YUUKO] Get a load of
this handsome stud!
[MIO gasps]
Wow! He looks so cool!
[gasping]
That's impressive!
I'd say you've got quite
the artistic talent there!
Aw, well it's not that amazing.
Oh wait, maybe it is.
[MIO sighs]
I think I'm gonna name my dapper
doodle dude Hubbu Hunkerson.
[IZUMI]
Wow! That's such a cool name!
[MIO gasps]
[MIO]
None of this is cool!
[MIO] I dunno guys, I think it
should look more like this.
--[MIO] Feast your eyes!
--[DRAWING A] Edgy!
Wow, amazing! It looks
like it's from a manga!
You must put a lot
of time and effort
into practicing your art skills.
[MIO]
Well, uh, just a little!
[IZUMI] Remarkable! Show me
some of your other work!
Uh. I don't think so.
[IZUMI]
Oh? But why not?
I would love to see
more of your stuff.
Um. Well. It's just...
[YUUKO growls]
Gimme that thing!
My drawing is way cooler
than yours, see?
[YUUKO humming]
You straight-up copied me!
You don't know that.
I saw you do it!
"Homage" may be the word
you're looking for.
So you're admitting
that you copied?!
Wow! That's so cool!
You are so easy to please!
All right, then, prepare
yourselves for some of this!
[MIO] Glasses! Every girl
swoons over the cool
and collected demeanor
behind those lenses!
Ah, so he wears glasses.
[MIO]
Huh?
Is his eyesight bad?
He'd probably look
better if he wore contacts.
[MIO] You two don't
understand anything!
[YUUKO]
Y'know? I'll add an extra bit!
There we go!
[MIO]
They're hanging under his ears!
You so stole my glasses idea!
[YUUKO] Tch. Tch. Tch.
They're sunglasses.
Wow! They're so cool!
Are you kidding me?!
Oh, yeah? Then how's this?
A butler! The perfect gentleman
who serves you tea and
follows your every command!
He'll treat you like the fine
young lady you are!
Huh. Glasses again?
I don't think I
understand the appeal.
[YUUKO laughs] Maybe you should
have taken my contacts idea.
[MIO gasps]
I feel like you're a bit out
of touch, Mio. Tell ya what.
I'll show you what being
cool is really all about.
Some of this, and some of that.
Check it.
[MIO screaming]
It's floating!
Wait! Hold on a sec!
Is he supposed to be driving?
Wow! He's so fast and dangerous!
[MIO]
You've gotta be kidding me!
They don't understand
coolness at all!
You wanna see something cool?
Then I'll have to show you.
This is a lesson now.
You're gonna see what
true coolness really is!
You'll see! You'll all see!
[MIO grunts]
This is the coolest!
[KOUJIROU]
Yo.
[IZUMI]
Uh...
[YUUKO]
[exhales]
[MIO]
Oh, no.
I'm just kidding!
[MIO laughs]
I kid!
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR] I drew
this while listening to jazz.
[YUUKO]
Good morning!
Oh. Oh, good morning,
all knowing master.
Don't you even!
[IZUMI]
Listen up class!
It's time for this
morning's quiz,
so take one and pass
it down, please.
[MIO]
Aw man, this sucks.
I was hoping that I could keep
my drawing skills a secret
for a while longer, and then
I had to go overboard.
All things considered,
after going berserk like that,
I should be relieved that what I
drew ended up as tame as it was.
I guess I should
count myself lucky.
But I'm sure I won't hear
the end of it from Yuuko,
at least for the next few
days. That's okay, though!
I gotta look on the bright side!
And stay positive!
[KOUJIROU]
Yo.
[YUUKO]
Hurry up and pass it back.
Uhh.
Ready, and... begin!
[YUUKO groaning]
[ONOMATOPOEIA]
Yoink! Bang! Zoom!
Hello! It's nice to meet you!
I'm an Onomatopoeia!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Now you try it!
But don't chicken out!
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 6.
Look forward to it!