[cicadas chirping]
[SAKAMOTO snoring]
[NANO]
Such a beautiful morning!
Guess I should go
wake Hakase up.
Maybe after breakfast,
I could take a quick stroll
around the block.
[whistling]
[NANO]
Hm?
Huh? Wait! Ahh!
Wait for me, you guys!
Selamat pagi !
Oh, hey, good morning, Yuuko.
Good morning.
Great day for a walk, huh?
Yeah! Even though the forecast
said it would rain.
I thought weather people
were usually right. But maybe,
they use a numpad to pad
their numbers! Ya get it?
[YUUKO]
Ah! What's wrong with them?
They're totally deadpan!
It's like they didn't
even hear me!
Am I invisible? Am I a ghost?
[gasps]
[YUUKO] Wait a sec. What if
my joke was too complicated
for them and they
didn't understand it?
Oh well, that's a shame.
It was such a good one.
But maybe I should try something
that's more their speed.
Not everyone can keep up
with my quick wit. Okay!
[YUUKO]
Man, it's gettin' kinda hot!
The clouds are patchy,
but I hope my hair isn't!
That'd be bad.
[YUUKO gasping]
[YUUKO] Okay! Now they're
really starting to freak me out!
I'm so spooked!
But I get it.
Sudden and irregular hair
loss is no laughing matter.
--I gotta keep it light.
--[NANO] Come back!
[YUUKO]
All right!
It's time to unleash
my secret weapon!
You better brace yourselves!
[YUUKO]
Hey, listen!
What do you call a thousand-leg
insect that asks for help?
You call it... a centiplead!
Get it?
[YUUKO] Still nothing?
How is that possible?
They've got the most
intense poker-faces
I've ever seen in my life!
[gasps]
[YUUKO] Hold up! What if
they just didn't get it
'cause they didn't know
I was telling jokes?
That's fine then.
It's nobody's fault! Well,
at least not mine. 'Kay!
Hey! It's joke time!
What do you call a thousand-leg
insect that asks for help?
You call it...
a centiplead! Get it now?
[YUUKO] That's the coldest
shoulder I've ever seen.
I never thought that they could
be total ice queens like this.
[gasps]
[YUUKO]
But what if...
Maybe...
This is their way of saying that
I need to get up to their level.
You know what? I will!
Watch me.
[YUUKO] Fine then!
I accept your challenge!
I'll show you what I
can do, just you wait!
You'll see! You'll all see!
All two of you!
[YUUKO groaning]
[YUUKO]
I can do this! I'll never...
...give up!
So Oxygen went on a
date with Potassium!
[YUUKO]
It went OK!
[rumbling]
[whimpers]
A fake noodle's an im-pasta!
A fat psychic's a
four-chin teller.
Ahh... I tried to catch the fog.
But I mist!
[AKAGI] So basically, you
can just substitute the X
in the equation, then
plug and chug the answer.
Then this Y over here...
[door clicks]
[OGI]
President.
[DAIKU]
Ogi!
It's been forever since you've
showed up to the club!
And I was starting to
think you abandoned me!
How've ya been? Good?
[OGI]
Uh. Yeah.
Well I'm really glad you
came back here, so hey!
Tell ya what! Let's
celebrate your return!
Come on. How 'bout
some Isei-no-sei?
Nah, I'm just here to quit.
[grunting]
[HAKASE yells]
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
Why do I always get the urge
to clear my throat just before
a movie is about to start?
[MISATO panting]
[WEBOSHII]
And then, I was all like--
[MISATO]
Weboshii! Fe!
Have you seen Sasahara?
The goat guy?
Oh! I think I actually saw him
heading up the stairs,
to the roof.
[MISATO]
'Kay, thanks!
Looks like somebody's in
a hurry. She's so smitten.
We should totes go
and follow her!
Those two might be up
to something spicy!
Oh!
[KOUJIROU] In the deep blue sky,
clouds drift and linger above.
It was a right hand.
Sasahara.
What a masterpiece!
[MISATO growls]
Hey, you dork!
Do you have any freakin'
idea what you've done?
Huh? Today's weather
appeared to be quite pleasant,
so I came to the roof
to write a poem about it.
[MISATO]
I'm talking about this!
That's right. Look here.
This thing ring any bells?
Huh. I do believe
that's one of mine.
I must wonder why it's
in your possession.
Don't act like you're innocent!
You were littering, so I
had to pick it up for you!
It's certainly not trash.
And I never meant
to throw it away.
I just dropped my
handkerchief by acci--
Yeah right! That thing is yours,
which means it's garbage!
If I dropped it, how did
you know it was mine?
We don't even walk
the same way to school.
[gasps]
[KOUJIROU] Huh, looks like
you ironed it for me, too.
[BOTH gasp]
Don't go assuming things!
You're so stupid!
I was just wandering around lost
in thought, and I happened to
find it on a street
somewhere near your house.
[BOTH gasping]
[KOUJIROU]
Hm.
I appreciate what you
did, Miss Tachibana.
[BOTH]
Uhh...
[MISATO] You drop a lot
of things in the morning,
all the time.
I suppose I've never
realized that. Good to know.
[MISATO]
Well, cut it out!
You'll cause problems
for the city if you don't!
[MISATO] But, uh, if you
keep dropping stuff,
I guess I can pick up after you.
[KOUJIROU]
Hm?
[BOTH gasping]
But don't get the wrong idea!
I'm only doing what's necessary
to keep the streets clean!
[ALL gasp]
[WEBOSHII] Dang, that Misato
never changes, does she?
[FE]
Hey um. What do I do with this?
[WEBOSHII]
Uh! Why'd you grab that thing?!
[FE] I didn't know
what to do with it!
[WEBOSHII]
Just leave it somewhere!
[FE]
But then what do I do?
[WEBOSHII]
Just leave it and walk away!
[FE] But then what
do I do after that?
[WEBOSHII]
Keep on walking!
[BOTH] Things we think
are freakin' cool!
[BOTH]
Super-car bicycle!
[YUUKO]
I give up. It's all over.
Help isn't coming.
[MIO]
There is no God.
There is no Buddha.
[YUUKO]
Yesterday...
...was pork cutlet bowls?
Oh, well. This is fine.
[insect buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
[YUUKO]
Huh?
How long has it been?
[MIO]
Oh, whoops. I think I...
...dozed off there.
Yeah. It's fine.
The word-chain game.
Wanna play?
Mandarin.
Oh. Sorry.
Say that again?
What would that be?
Be.
Be...
Uh, can I just say
any random word?
Eggplant.
[grunting]
[exhales, laughs]
Heh... Heh. Heh.
[laughs]
[BOTH exhale, laugh]
[BOTH laughing]
Eggplant!
[MIO laughing]
She's dead!
Help isn't coming!
[BOTH laughing]
[MIO]
Isn't coming!
[MAI]
Guess I'll die.
[laughing continues]
[DAIKU groans]
It looks like the club is down
to just you and me again.
We'll have to disband if we
can't find a third member
to join us sometime soon.
If only we could make the club
more appealing to
recruit more members.
--Question.
--[DAIKU] Huh?
[SEKIGUCHI]
What do we even do in this club?
Oh, right!
That's what we have to figure
out to make us more appealing!
We kinda don't do anything.
[MIO]
On your mark...
Get set...
[MIO]
Go!
[YUUKO grunts]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
[CROWD cheering]
[SEKI]
Hey! Cut it out, dude!
Let go of my jersey!
[GOTO]
Come on, bro, just relax!
Lemme take it off for you!
[SEKI]
I can't do that, dude!
I didn't score at all today!
Not a single point!
It's fine, bro! It's not
like you'll need this
old uniform after
you retire anyway!
[SEKI]
Just hear me out, dude!
My uniform won't
be worth anything
if I'm a player that's
never scored!
[GOTO]
That's not true, bro!
You inspired me to play ball
and that's worth it to me!
[SEKI] All right, dude,
all right, fine, I'll do it!
I can take if off myself!
Just like, uh, let me
go so I can do it!
[GOTO]
Uhh...
All right, ya got me.
Psych!
[GOTO]
Hey uh, sorry, bro.
[SAKAMOTO]
Listen up!
I'm gonna remind you again that
you need to respect your elders.
'Kay...
[SAKAMOTO] As always,
she can be such a pawful.
Hm? Oh!
[SAKAMOTO grunts]
[SAKAMOTO]
Oh, man, this is too fun!
C'mere tail!
[DAIKU] At first, I wanted
to make a sport that captured
the best parts of
Go and Soccer.
So... That's why I
made a club for it.
[DAIKU]
But...
I got nothin'.
[HAKASE]
Draw a boomerang shape.
Then a triangle shape,
then a rectangle shape.
Hakase! It's time to go to bed!
[HAKASE]
'Kay!
[NANO growls] You weren't
just eating snacks were you?
I didn't eat any snacks.
[NANO] Why are you
looking to the side?
I'll look the other
way to even it out.
[NANO]
That doesn't make sense.
Ah-ha! See!
Why are you snacking
after I told you not to?
I, uh, wasn't the one
who ate those snacks!
If you didn't eat them,
why do you have crumbs
all over your face?
[gasps]
[HAKASE coughs]
I think I've caught a cold.
[NANO]
Enough! I'm not playing around!
When I say no, it means no!
And you're not listening!
Not one bit!
It's not my fault!
Sakamoto forced me to eat
all of the yummy snacks!
[laughs] He's got a little
snot bubble. That's gross.
[NANO]
Don't try to change the subject!
[NANO] Jeez. You need remember
to brush your teeth before bed.
I already brushed 'em!
Huh? Did you brush them again
after you had snacks?
I did. Extra good.
[NANO] What are you
so embarrassed about?
[HAKASE]
It's fine!
Brushing once a night
is all I need to do!
No, it's not! You brush
after you eat.
Well, did you brush
after my snack?!
I don't have to. I didn't eat!
Uh! Then, uh...
[NANO] I'm all ready to go
to bed, and you're not.
Now go brush before
you get cavities.
[HAKASE grumbles, sniffs]
You're a robot, so you
can't even get cavities!
[NANO gasping]
[HAKASE]
Ah! Wait, uh!
I mean, um, that I just, uh.
Maybe you can get a tiny cavity.
Can I really?
Uh, yeah sure.
[NANO]
Uhh! You're lying.
[HAKASE]
Oh! But you can still
get other grody
stuff, like rust!
--[NANO] I'll rust.
--[HAKASE] Okay, uh!
I'll add a feature that
lets you get cavities!
I promise! It'll be
the best feature ever!
Do you really swear?
[gasps] You can count on me!
[HAKASE]
Come on, Nano!
Let's go and brush
our teeth again!
[NANO] Okay. But you know
I don't have to, right?
[HAKASE]
Whoa! It's already ten o'clock!
[NANO]
It sure is.
[HAKASE]
Today was a blast!
[NANO]
Yeah, yeah.
[HAKASE]
I had so much fun!
[MISATO]
Man.
I wish Sasahara would just take
things seriously for once.
[YOLK A] We're a double-yolk
egg! Like twins!
[YOLK B]
Twinning!
[YOLK A]
Ow! Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
[YOLK B]
Hot! It's hot!
Th-The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 9!
Ouch! Look forward
to-- Ah, ah, hot!