[TANAKA]
Man, it's so hot out.
Super-duper hot!
Ah. Can you cut
it out? I feel it.
This heat has been
hard on me, too.
But ya know, when you bring it
up, it makes it worse, 'kay?
So could you stop
saying it's hot?
Okay, okay.
Man, it's a scorcher out here!
It's blistering.
Sweltering, even!
Do ya know what I mean, man?
Feels like I'm in an oven!
I'm baking out here! Broiling!
So humid!
[NAKANOJOU]
I could punch him right now.
Nobody would know.
[TANAKA]
What's with the sun?
This gotta be a record!
Dude, seriously,
it is like fire!
[humming]
[YUUKO]
What a beautiful day!
The sky is blue,
birds are chirping,
butterflies are fluttering.
The air, the people, and yes,
even this very classroom.
Everything is great!
Because... I actually did
the homework for today!
[giggles]
[YUUKO] I bet Mio willl get
a real kick outta this.
[humming]
[YUUKO]
Huh?
Hang on. Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
No!
[screaming]
[YUUKO] It can't be!
You've gotta be kidding me!
The one time I actually
did my homework?
Why?
Why did this have
to happen? Why me?
Oh, well, guess I'll just
have to copy it again.
Hey, Mio, question!
[YUUKO]
Hm?
Wait, our homework.
That's right. We had to...
fill in a worksheet!
[YUUKO crying]
What's the matter with you?
Did something happen, Yuuko?
[YUUKO]
My homework. I left it at home.
There's no hope. There's
nothing good in this world.
But you always forget
to do your homework.
It's different this time!
I did it, but I didn't bring it!
[MIO]
Uh, yeah, okay I hear ya.
It's the worksheet we
got yesterday, right?
You sure it isn't jammed
inside your bag somewhere?
Check one more time to see.
I just turned this whole thing
inside-out and got nothing.
There's no way it's--
[gasps]
Whoa!
My God!
Ah! What the hell
is a Daifuku Fair?!
What's fair? Nothing.
[MIO]
Uh, don't worry about it.
Hey, who knows?
Maybe there's an extra that
was left on the front desk.
Are you for real?
It's a miracle!
[YUUKO]
Dammit!
Dammit, dammit! Damn all of it!
Are you going back home?
But there's no time!
You're right.
But I have to... try!
[BOTH]
Uh.
Where are you off to
in such a hurry?
Go and take your seats.
[grunting]
[gasps]
[HAKASE]
Twisty, twisty, twisty, twisty,
twisty, twisty, spinning,
and spinning...
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
Slow and steady wins the race.
[YUUKO]
Out in the hall again.
Why is it that I can
never get my homework in?
Am I cursed?
I always end up failing.
Even when I actually finish it.
School is a cruel mistress.
[HAKASE]
Hey, Sakamoto.
[SAKAMOTO]
Hm?
Look at my business card.
[HAKASE giggles]
[SAKAMOTO] Uh? What is
this about? What do I say?
[HAKASE chuckles]
[SAKAMOTO]
What's happening?
[chuckling]
[SAKAMOTO] What am I
supposed to do with this?
[MISATO]
Excuse me!
[MISATO gasps]
[KOUJIROU] What seems to be
the problem, Miss Tachibana?
[MISATO]
Uh, nothing!
The vending machine
got some new drinks,
and I was just deciding
on which one I wanted.
Oh. Is that so?
Well, then, I recommend--
[MISATO] I don't need you
to tell me what to get!
...you stay away
from this option,
but the one next to it is
actually quite refreshing.
Enjoy your drink.
It's not like I bought this
drink because you pointed at it!
[ANNAKA]
I heard the neighborhood had
some pop-up stalls, so I
decided to check them out.
I am so excited that
this game is here.
A carnival shooting gallery!
I've never seen
one in real life!
But all I have on me
is a 500 yen coin.
I hope it'll be enough.
[GAME RUNNER A] Step right up!
One round is 500 yen!
[ANNAKA]
Perfect!
Isn't that convenient?!
I wish I had enough
for some yakisoba , too.
But this'll be worth it.
[gasps]
[ANNAKA] There's only
caramels and eggplants?
Uh... Do you have
any other prizes?
Whaddaya mean other prizes?
We've only got the finest
quality, brand-name goods here!
[GAME RUNNER A laughing]
[ANNAKA]
He already took my money,
so I might as well go for it.
Don't wanna leave empty handed.
[gasps]
Nice try, Miss,
but you shouldn't shoot for
the grand prize right away.
Beginner's luck won't
help you with that one!
[ANNAKA]
Grand prize?
Why don't you aim for
something smaller?
It's prob'ly more your speed!
Go ahead!
[ANNAKA]
More my speed?
Whatever. Might as well go
for the only other option.
[gasps, yells]
So close!
[ANNAKA] Okay, that box
has to be glued down.
Just a little more you
and woulda had it.
Looks like you're a pretty good
sharpshooter there, Miss!
Don't tell me. You're not a
professional gunman, are you?
Yeah, as if!
[laughing]
[ANNAKA] Ah! That thing
isn't budging an inch!
Oh, no. What're you
making that face for?
You aren't thinking that the
game is rigged, now are you?
Yeah, my stall might not be
the fanciest one out there,
but an honest and genuine
experience is guaranteed!
[ANNAKA]
Yeah, right.
There's definitely something
fishy going on here.
[yelps]
What is that?
Ah! Look! Right in the middle!
There's a nail! You totally
nailed down that eggplant!
I'd call this whole thing
a racket, wouldn't you?
Come on! Why are you giving
me the silent treatment now?
Have you no shame for preying
on innocent people?
I bet this entire
operation is rigged!
And what happened to
all that big talk
you were spewing earlier, huh?
What's the point in
pretending to sleep?
I've still got one shot left
and I have a pretty good
idea where to put it!
[ANNAKA]
Hm?
[GAME RUNNER A]
Don't ever come back.
[ANNAKA]
Like I'd want to.
[MIO, YUUKO] Things we
think are freakin' cool!
Ready, Mio? Here it comes!
[MIO gasps]
[squeals]
Hey, nice catch!
[YUUKO, MIO]
Wow! Super bouncy balls!
[YUUKO, MIO] Things we
think are freakin' cool!
Aw! I had it!
[BOTH yelp]
[YUUKO, MIO]
Wow!
Slipstreams! Created by cards!
Thanks a bunch!
I haven't been to an
amusement park in forever!
Right? This is so fun!
Hey, hand me my wallet,
I'm gonna get a drink.
Oh. Yeah, sure. I totally
forgot I was holding on to it.
[YUUKO]
Thanks for that.
But you know me;
I'd probably lose it.
Ha! Yeah, I guess that's true.
[MIO]
Hm?
Wait, wha...?
Just hold on a second.
AH! Because I know it's
inside this zipper pocket,
or maybe that one.
Hang on, I know I
put it in my bag.
It should be right
here, but it's not,
so maybe I might have...
I kinda, sorta, definitely
lost your wallet.
[MIO gasps]
I know!
Why don't we check
the Lost and Found!
Maybe someone turned it in!
How much did you have in there?
[YUUKO]
Four thousand and sixteen yen.
[MIO]
That's specific.
Uh, we're looking for
a brown bifold wallet.
And it has a snakeskin interior.
[MAN A]
Ah, we have one just like it.
[gasps]
That was close. Aren't
you glad we found it?
Yeah.
I dunno what I would've actually
done if I lost everything.
[ANNOUNCER A] Attention:
This is an announcement
regarding a lost child.
Please listen carefully.
A young girl has been found.
She is wearing a denim shirt
that is tucked
into denim shorts.
Her hat is also made of denim.
She is currently looking
for her mother.
If you have any information,
please come to the lost
child station immediately.
[PEOPLE laughing]
[PEOPLE screaming]
I have no clue why I thought
a stupid haunted house
was a good idea!
--[bang]
--[yelps]
[MIO screaming]
[MIO laughing]
'Kay, say cheese!
[laughs]
Your order is three lattes.
Is there anything
else you'd like?
Oh, uh! I think...
I'd like this one, this one,
and this one please.
Uh. I'm terribly sorry, miss.
But could you please provide
a specific name for the orders?
[gasps] Oh, it's Sakurai.
Uh, that's not exactly
what I meant.
[IZUMI]
Oh, no! I'm so sorry!
It's Izumi. The name's
Izumi Sakurai.
Sorry, but I wasn't asking
for your full name, either.
[IZUMI]
Sorry!
I've been told it sounds like
I have two last names,
so I thought you were confused.
Well, I didn't mean your name.
All I need is the names of
the items that you want.
Huh? You want names
of the items?
I'm sorry, but I don't
know what they are.
Oh! No. It's okay.
I'm sorry for the trouble!
Yum, that food hit the spot!
I'm officially stuffed!
But I still have some room
left in my dessert stomach.
Same here.
[MIO gasps]
Cool! I'll do one too!
[MIO]
Here's mine!
I'm done, too.
Whoa! Awesome! Your
stuff's great as usual.
What did you make? Done yet?
[groans]
[MIO]
A crane?
[HAKASE]
Nano! Check it out!
Ta-da!
I put a big key on my back, too!
Isn't this cool? Now we're
matching and stuff.
Yeah, I guess we are.
Since I'm like you now,
I'm gonna be Nano all day,
so no calling me "Hakase," okay?
Okay, "Nano," you got it.
[SAKAMOTO]
Meow-ch!
[NANO]
Already?
Uh, Hakase, did you quit, or...?
It's "Nano"! I'm being
you right now!
Oh, well, I just figured
since you took
the key off of your back.
I'm just giving my back
a break right now.
I'm still Nano all day today.
Right. Understood.
[sighs]
[gasps]
Hey, Hakase--I mean, "Nano."
I have an idea for
a game we can play!
Do ya? What'cha got?
Since you're being me,
then why don't we switch places
and I can be you today?
You bet!
[NANO]
So then, Hakase--I mean, Nano,
would have to put her key on.
Sure!
[chuckles]
[NANO]
And since I'm Hakase now,
that means I should get
this key off my back.
Not a chance.
So, what do you wanna play
first? Like cards or something?
[HAKASE yelps]
Wow, these snacks are yummy!
Those are mine! And I was
saving them for later!
But now... I'm Hakase...
so I get all your snacks.
Ah! That doesn't make any sense!
I can Nano, but if Nano is me
and gets to eat my snacks,
then I don't wanna
be Nano anymore,
and Nano can just
stay being Nano.
[SAKAMOTO]
Keep it down.
[sighs]
Since everything is back to
normal and I'm Nano again,
I guess I'm gonna
go to the store
and get groceries
for tonight's dinner.
[HAKASE]
Huh? I wanna go, too!
[NANO] We're not gonna buy
any snacks while we're out.
[HAKASE]
I'm gonna get a chocolate shark
and some apple juice!
[NANO]
Not a chance.
--[HAKASE] Oh, come on!
--[NANO] No way.
[HAKASE]
Just the chocolate shark then!
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome Household.
[slurping]
The first one that says
anything loses the game.
Okay.
Oh. You just said something,
so that means you lost.
You didn't say when
we were starting,
so technically, I'm fine.
You wanna talk about
some random stuff
to get it out of our
system before we start?
You have anything you
wanna talk about?
Okay.
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
Carbonation makes drinks fizzy,
which really seems
to wake you up.
I was out.
Good morning.
It looks like sleeping beauty
woke up without her kiss.
[YUUKO]
Hm?
That sucks.
[gasps]
And why is that?
[CIDER]
Welcome home, Master!
It's me, Cider!
I know my bubbly personality
is intoxicating,
so twist off the cap,
wiff the fizz,
and join my carbon-nation.
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 13!
Look forward to it!