A-A-A-choo!
It sure is getting cold lately. Huh?
Wha...?
Sakamoto.
Stop it! Stay back!
Cut it out! Wait!
Just hold on a second!
Leave me alone!
You're freakin' me out!
At least--tell me why you're doing this.
Okay, Mai. You can apply the screentones on this one.
Yuuko, take those and use the pen
to draw in the appropriate page numbers in the corners.
And fill in the shade of the character's hair, too.
Okay!
Amazing!
I had no idea you were so proficient in creating manga!
I'm nothing special, so I wouldn't put it that way.
She's actually been drawing forever,
but kept it a secret until recently.
Well, it's not secret anymore, is it?
But why did you hide it?
Just 'cause.
But now,
I guess I don't really think it's that big of a deal
if people find out about what I like to do.
Things kinda got put into perspective
after I submitted to a manga magazine.
They said that they were looking forward
to my next submission,
so I figured there's no point
in keeping it a secret anymore.
That means they think you're talented enough
to get published one day!
Let's not jump to conclusions yet.
Is it okay if I take a look at some of your work?
Uh...
Um... Nano?
You okay?
Uhh. Hey, don't force it.
You don't have to read it if it's not to your taste.
What's the matter?
Um, excuse me.
I think I need to get some fresh air.
I can come with you if you want company.
It's fine.
I don't want to distract you guys
from working on the manuscript,
so just keep on keeping on.
I'll be back in a little while, okay?
Huh. I guess there must be a lot on her mind, huh?
Aw, crap!
It's this late already?
We really can't afford to waste any more time now!
Let's buckle down and focus!
No more playing around.
We gotta hit that deadline tomorrow.
You got it, boss lady!
I dunno if you know this, but I'm quite the artist myself,
so this'll be easy-peasy!
Everybody to battle stations!
Or something.
Come on, Yuuko.
You just started and you're slacking off already?
Here.
Whoa, that was quick.
All right, I'll check it over.
Now let's see what we got here.
I'll make you a slave.
A what?
Are you kidding me? Why did you draw this?
It's Kuya the Monk.
I don't have time for your stupid pranks!
What made you think you had to add things?
The blank page called out, longing to be filled.
What does that mean?!
Take the white out and fix it as fast as possible. Please.
Just stick to the screentones like I asked.
And stop vandalizing my art!
I've experienced a lot of pain in my life,
but that had to be the absolute worst. Ever.
I better get to work.
Uh--huh?
Huh?
Oh, no.
Wait! This is bad!
Crap, crap, crap, crap, crap, crap, crap, crap, crap, crap!
Oh, yeah, and--
If you make any mistakes, make sure to tell me right away
so I can fix it before it gets any worse.
Any worse?
Ooh, it can't get any worse than this, right?
So, I might as well try to fix it!
It's done.
Oh? Already?
I hope you didn't add anything
weird to the background again.
I'll make you a grave.
A what?
It's a grave now?!
What even is this?
A graveyard.
That was a rhetorical question!
That background's supposed to
be a fancy palace in Daikanyama!
So? Why didn't you just draw that?
Why'd it have to be something weird?
Because there was empty space left over.
You're the absolute worst!
Just forget it!
Erase it and I'll do it myself later!
You can only erase, no adding!
Am I making myself clear?
Understood.
There.
That doesn't look too bad!
I mean, I'm sure it'd be fine if I drew it on its own,
but right now... it doesn't match!
Mio is gonna kill me, isn't she?
I'm finished.
I hope you only erased things like I asked.
Ugh, whatever.
My characters better not still
be on that weird background.
Why?! What did you do?
I erased.
I'm about to erase you here in a second!
Why do you keep messing with my artwork like this?
Because I don't think the manga you're making
is very interesting.
I'm asking for your help, not your opinion!
Forget the erasing and just
take this and draw some panels.
Make sure they match the other page!
You got it, boss lady.
You better not screw this one up!
Helvetica Standard.
Now ten seconds.
Twenty seconds.
And one, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
The time is up.
This is not going well!
I don't even know
what the heck he's supposed to look like anymore!
Who is he?
Where did he come from?
Mio is definitely gonna kill me now!
I'm finished.
Okay...
And you only drew the panels, right?
Long, long ago,
there lived an ordinary man and woman.
The man ventured out to gather firewood.
The Private second class was born from a peach.
That makes no sense!
Will you please just follow instructions?
I can do that.
♪ Cha-cha-la-la! Cha! ♪
♪ Cha-cha-cha-cha Cha-la-la! ♪
Thi... is... the worst!
I'm trying my best to fix things,
but it gets uglier every time I touch it.
This is a pickle.
What should I do?
What can I do?
Wait, Mai?
Just leave it to me.
You mean you can fix it?
You can draw? Seriously?
Of course she can't.
There's no way.
That'd be too good to be true.
Wait! Unless...
...she's good!
She is, like, crazy good!
Maybe she's too crazy!
But, right now,
if crazy is what it takes, then let's get crazy!
Let's go back to the good ol' days.
Back when I didn't know the difference
between right and wrong.
When everything was fresh and innocent.
And then, tell the truth and be set free.
I'm so sorry!
You'll have to draw this section over again!
But...
We don't have any manuscript paper left!
Hey, wait.
No running in the hallway.
Sasahara!
Dammit, it won't come off!
They wanted nothing at all.
Gotcha!
Hey, Yoshino.
What are you doing here?
Looking for me?
I just stopped by, same as you.
Okay...
So, what are you up to?
Um, well, uh, nothing, I guess.
Really?
Actually... It's just...
I can't concentrate during practice,
and we have the competition coming up.
I'm not sure if you've ever felt anything like this
when you were in high school,
but I feel like it's getting harder and harder
to keep my guard up sometimes.
She's not listening.
Have you ever read this manga before?
It's hilarious!
For real? She's not helpful with anything but kendo.
Not surprised.
What? Quit muttering!
What were you saying?
Don't worry about it!
By the way, you were planning on
being at the national kendo championship,
isn't that right?
Oh! Yeah, I am.
If that's true,
then how come Mihoshi's been saying
that you haven't been to the dojo in--
I forgot I have to go grocery shopping today!
Huh? W-Wait, hang on!
You can have my rice crackers.
Thanks?
See ya!
What was that all about?
Hey, Sis!
What are ya doin'?
Just chillin' here?
I was, uh, just talking to Yoshino.
Even though the national championship's tomorrow?
Hold on. Tomorrow?
Did she mention anything?
Mm... Not really.
Wait! She left me these things.
Want one?
Sure.
Wow, its red.
It sure is.
Spicy!
I don't think so!
What do you mean?
I'm not sure!
Hey, Mio. Turn around. I want you to see this!
Huh?
You like my new look?
I've been wanting to change things up,
so I bought some of these thingies the other day.
You like 'em?
Yeah, they suit you.
♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ Not ready yet! ♪
♪ Are you ready now? ♪
♪ I'm ready! ♪
Okay!
Then ready or not, here I come!
Oh, Hakase!
Where are you?
♪ I'm ready! ♪
Sakamoto has been caught!
Huh?
Beginner's luck is a hell of a thing. Whatever.
If you say so.
I usually don't reduce myself
to playing with kids like you,
but sometimes the boredom can be a little too much.
Right.
What are you waiting for?
Don't just sit there!
Let's go play some more!
--All right! --Shabadaba-doo!
Hakase?
Where are you?
Hey, kid! You there?
Come on out!
Who knew she'd be so good at hiding.
She really did disappear, huh?
They're never, ever gonna find me in here.
Knowing her, I'd wager that she's
probably hiding somewhere outside.
That makes sense.
But maybe we should take a break.
Sounds good.
It's just as well.
I dunno about you,
but I'd be fine with never finding her!
Whoa, there you are.
Did you build this room all by yourself?
Mm-hmm.
Why'd you come out of such a good hiding spot?
There's no point in us seeking if you don't hide.
Get it?
I was scared that you wouldn't be able to
find me in my secret room and I'd be hiding forever.
Well, that's a good point.
Hakase.
Did you... blow your nose on me?
Yeah.
Now I'm gonna have to
put my school uniform in the laundry, too.
Then I guess that settles it.
Looks like I'll be it this time!
Sound good? Ready, set, go!
I can help you wash your school uniform if you want.
That'll probably just make things worse,
so I think I'll pass.
You won't know for sure till you try!
No, I think I'm pretty sure about this one.
Aw, come on! It'll be fine!
The Life of Pyon!
Check him out!
That's it. No more excuses!
I can't believe you!
Well, yeah, uh, I was saying--
I don't care what you have to say!
You coming over to help out
was a nice gesture and everything.
I get that.
But all you did was make things worse for me.
And then, after I said that we were out of paper,
instead of going out and getting more,
you had to make it difficult.
Do you remember that?
I asked you to go buy some, and what did you say?
Hey, how's about we flip for it?
Take it off our hands... and leave it to fate!
Not a chance in hell!
You're the one who spilled all
the ink and ruined the page.
How could you even consider making me go
when I have so much work to do? Come on!
But I got over it!
You ended up agreeing with me
and you said you'd be the one to go to the store.
And then what did you have to say?
Mio, I, uh...
What did you say?
Question.
Judging by my face, how old do I look?
Who cares?!
You just keep wasting my time
and the paper store's gonna close!
Why bring that up now of all times?
Why would you ask me that?
But I got over it!
You finally decided to head off to the store,
and what did you suddenly have to complain about?
It sure is chilly out.
Oh, speaking of, I think I might've caught a cold.
How could you have caught a cold out of nowhere?!
You just kept on wasting my time!
And--it's not even that cold out!
But I got over it!
And? What did you come back with in hand?
The hell is that anyway?!
All you had to do was get the manuscript paper
like I asked!
But you had to make your stupid jokes!
And you just could never tell when enough was enough!
Here.
That's a hard pass for me!
I thought I was at the end of my rope with you,
but you keep finding more rope to cut!
Especially when you don't stop
coming up with dumb things to say!
I'm so sorry, calamari.
Calamari?!
This isn't even funny anymore!
Where the hell did calamari come from anyway?
And after all that,
I still actually believed that
you got the manuscript paper.
But it was some esoteric joke that gave me a headache!
All I wanted was for you to hurry up and get the paper,
but what did you say to that?
Sorry for the delay. Please frog-ive me.
It's a frog now?!
Are you actually asking for forgiveness?
Or are you asking me to give you a frog?
I ask you one final time
if you actually got any of the manuscript paper,
and what did you have to say to that?
Sorry safari.
Where'd safari come from and what happened to calamari?!
Wait, who cares about calamari?
Where is my paper?
Oh, yeah! You gave me something else!
--Here. --Writing paper. Indeed.
Now I have all the tools I need... for my novel.
Wrong kind of paper!
How long do you intend to make a joke out of my life
until you're satisfied?
What do you want from me, huh?
Oh wait, you said--!
You know, there's a funny thing about the truth.
It's not always true.
Yes, it is!
I decided you were a lost cause
and I had no choice but to turn to Nano.
But I messed up and showed her my work in progress.
And then she--!
She got hooked!
Thanks, but no thanks!
She just can't stop squealing!
I got so desperate, I even asked Mai for help!
Mai, could you do me a favor and get me some more paper?
But she bounced already!
She vanished like the wind!
Flowing swiftly yet silently at her own pace!
Sure, it was kind of disrespectful,
but that's not the point!
The point is, you saw the goodbye letter she left behind,
and you said what?
This could be a sign from God,
or the trap of a demon.
You're the demon who's trapping me!
This entire day has been a trap
since you showed up to quote-unquote "help"!
And it just kept on going and going!
I don't even get that one!
--Uh, you know-- --Shut up!
I don't wanna hear any more excuses from you!
You're just a pumpkin head!
Hang on, now.
Don't go nuts.
I'm only going nuts because you're making me!
You dumb...
...giant peanut head!
I'm trying to tell you--
Don't try to give me another one of your--
Your--
Huh?
Uh...
I'm sorry.
Please... frog-ive me?
Hello!
I'm the medium of your dreams, Manga Manuscript Paper.
Draw your heart out and achieve fame,
shooting me through the mail service of your choice.
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 21.
Walk-ins are welcome, too.