Green light...
And red light.
This is bad! Really, really bad!
Homeroom's starting and I'm so freakin' late!
Gotta come up with a really good excuse!
I can't say I stopped to help an old lady,
or that my mom didn't wake me up on time--
I used those already!
What's believable?
And what'll for sure get me out of trouble?
What was even the point of the red light?!
How did I hit every single stop light
on the way over?
Thanks to that, I have to awkwardly show up
in the middle of first period!
What's with the booby trap?
As if I'd fall for such a basic prank.
Ah! A two-fer?
What kind of cruel and unusual punishment is this?
I didn't even do anything wrong! Besides being late.
It's a good thing I can just slip in
through the little side door here.
At least that saves me the embarrassment
of getting chewed out at the front of the classroom.
Yup. Of course it's locked.
It just had to be locked today of all days!
I know! I can just sneak through the bottom door thingy!
I'll just slip in like the wind, completely undetected,
and they'll be none the wiser.
What is going on?
I should've known!
There's only one mastermind in this entire school
who'd do this and she's in my class.
I guess it could be for the best.
If I crawled through there,
I'd probably get into even more trouble.
But if I'm gonna go down,
I might as well take the high road!
Since when do we have stained-glass windows?
Hang on, why am I running?
There's nothing to run away from.
I've got no choice but to go back and face the music.
It's the right thing to do.
Looks like there's only one way this can go
that works out for me.
If I am to perish, I shall accept my fate proudly.
I'll march in through the front
door and go out with a bang.
That would be awesome!
Now, it's show time!
Prepare yourself, eraser.
You're gonna smack this class clown
with a giant grin on her face!
Sorry I'm late, but I erased to get here!
Everyone will think I'm hilarious!
Do you have any idea what time it is, young lady?
But I just can't stay mad at you.
Go ahead and take your seat, ya rascal!
I got this! I totally got this!
I am beauty. I am grace.
I shall appear...
...with a smile on my face!
Good morning, my fellow classmates!
I'm here and ready to start the tardy party!
I'm an invincible alien!
What stupid crap are you up to this time?
Aren't you a little old to be messing around like this?
People from planet Invincible are safe
from every sort of attack!
Hey! Uh. Heads up! I guess!
Would you shut up?!
Miles Davis is rolling in his grave!
I'm so sorry!
I guess we got a little bit carried away there, huh?
So what'd you think of our sound, cool cat?
It was pure torture!
And the only "sound" I could hear
was the rupturing of my ear drums!
Maybe you'll change your mind if I play it again.
Did you hear a word I said?!
Heh?
Looks like there's gonna be flowing noodles
at the park by the shrine today.
Guess I'll check it out!
I've only ever seen it done on TV,
but I bet it'll be super neat
to do it myself in real life!
Gotta try and get a good spot at the front,
or I might miss out on the noodly goodness!
I haven't eaten at all today,
so I gotta make sure to snag a
buncha noods and eat my fill!
Uh...
Noodles!
What the hell are you doing?!
Are you trying to screw things up?!
Here comes some more.
Um, excuse me, but I don't, uh...
What?!
Are you gonna show up here, waste my noodles,
and just give up?
I don't know who you think you are,
but that ain't gonna fly with me!
Uhh...
So, don't be mad,
but, uh, I don't have any chopsticks with me.
You're quite the demanding brat, huh?!
Here, you better be ready now!
Okay.
Eww...
Sorry to bother you,
but I think these are kinda-sorta used already.
Deal with it.
Enough chatter! My noodles wait for no one, get it?
Oh, well, guess I have no choice.
Aww.
When I dish out a joke, you're supposed to laugh.
The next one coming up will be different,
and I'll show you what true hell is like!
So get ready!
Uhh...
I'm not gonna waste all my water on you!
It's dry noodle or no noodle!
Don't you even think about skipping them.
I, uh...
Would you quit being so flaky?
Dig in and savor the flavor of raw noodles!
Uhh...
What are you waiting for?!
They won't stay fresh all day, y'know!
You haven't changed one bit.
Uh?
Y-You came back.
Uh...?
Masaharu!
When I caught word of the flowing noodles in the park,
I knew it had to be you.
I only did it all this time because I knew
that you would come back to me someday.
It's been 30 years since you left to search
for the most delicious flowing noodles.
Were you able to find them?
Huh?
I sampled noodles from all across the land,
but I'm afraid that it was all for naught.
I used our savings to support my travels,
but I must report, they're as dry as an uncooked nood.
Eh?
I'm sorry.
Could you ever accept a broken man without his noodles?
Huh?!
Of course.
What are you lookin' at?! Keep on walking!
Excuse me, miss,
but could you make like a flowing noodle and slip away?
Huh?!
Listen up, freshman, it's announcement time!
There are some people who learn with praise
and others who learn through criticism.
And I will be the one to determine which type you are,
you understand me?
When you learn through praise,
but never get praised.
Eight. Seven. Six. Five.
Four. Three. Two. One. Zero.
Launch when I say it like that!
Wait, what?
Seriously?! Why?!
Nano!
Look at what I did! I put my hair in a ponytail!
Oh...
What do you think?
It makes you look a lot more mature
when you put your hair up like that.
Uh! Really?
Okay, so can you tell me more about
how grown up you think I've gotten?
Yeah, okay.
I guess you seem more mature than you used to be?
How about you?
How grown up do you think you are, Nano?
Huh?
Well, I suppose I've never thought of myself
as the particularly mature type.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess you aren't all that mature, huh?
So, it looks like I have to be the one who cleans up!
Pick up this, and this.
Here, I'll grab that for you!
Um, I was still reading that. You don't have to take it.
Oh, silly Nano. Uh.
Uhh...
What am I gonna do with you, Sakamoto? Huh?
Uh, what're you doing?
I don't want you to catch a cold.
I dunno what you're up to,
but leave me out of it.
Oh, silly Sakamoto.
What?
You'll catch a cold.
No, I won't!
And if you're gonna cover me, use a towel or a blanket,
not a stupid book!
Oh, Sakamoto. Always so quick to complain.
Cut it out!
I do not appreciate this harassment!
All right, I'm gonna go and put the laundry in.
Hey! Good idea! Let's do it!
I've got this covered, Hakase.
All that's left to do now is turn on the dial.
Then it looks like I have no choice.
I'll turn the dial for you!
No. Don't worry. I can handle this part by myself.
I said I can turn it,
so lemme turn the dial thing, 'cause I wanna!
Okay, sure.
Could you please help me with the laundry?
If you need my help, you just have to ask.
Right. Sounds good.
Oh, well.
It looks like you're having trouble with the cooking,
so let me take care of it.
Actually, I think things are going fine on my end.
I bet my cooking will taste better if you try it!
Come on, I'll prove it to you!
Cut it out! That's dangerous!
Just lemme use the thingy!
I'm serious! You need to be careful!
--Come on! --Let go!
--You can trust me-- --Or else its gonna--
Oh my goodness! Is everything okay, Sakamoto?
Do things look okay to you?!
No! But I was just hoping!
You are so reckless, Sakamoto,
walking straight into harm's way like that.
How is this my fault?!
You were the ones messing around!
Try to relax, kitty-kitty. Being mad isn't helping anyone.
You are making zero sense right now!
It's not a big deal. I'll just start over.
Don't worry! You can leave all the cooking to me!
Well, I don't want all the other food to get cold,
so it needs to be quick.
Yeah, I get it.
I'll have to take care of things then.
Watch the eggs, Hakase!
You're gonna knock 'em over like that!
Don't worry so much! I'm grown up!
Hey! Careful!
I have everything under control!
Oh, clumsy kitty.
It's your fault!
Ugh. What is her deal today, anyway?
I think she's trying to act mature for us.
Because I am mature.
Psh.
Oh. Hey, kid.
Yeah, what's up?
You do know that mature kids don't get snacks.
Ta-dah! It was actually the same
ol' Hakase this entire time!
I lied.
Wha...?
Hm?
Whoa! It looks like I've got a big one!
Wow! A single rain boot!
Hm?
Ah! It's a giant one this time!
Whoa! It's an old tea kettle!
This is starting to feel more like
treasure hunting than fishing.
If I knew I'd find such cool stuff,
I would've brought some friends.
I guess I'll come back later.
Some trendy things.
Bare-handed sushi.
Dammit!
I don't wanna do my homework!
Why does homework even exist in the first place?
Well, my grades are in the crapper right now,
so I kinda have to do it.
I'm usually so good at doing just enough to scrape by.
Usually.
But right now...
...I'm wondering what I'll even do
if I graduate and go off to college.
What comes next? Getting a job?
I keep hearing about how tough the job market is nowadays,
so what chance do I have if I don't get my degree?
High school... College... Career...
The biggest hurdle right now
would be college entrance exams.
But... studying is the worst!
How is this school work applicable to real life anyway?
Wait, hang on.
What do I even want out of life?
"My dreams for the future" by Yuuko Aioi!
What do I want to be when I grow up?
I wanna be a frilled lizard, 'cause they're cool!
I'm... a Lizard.
La, la, la, la, la.
I don't wanna study!
I don't wanna be a frilled lizard anymore either,
so I'm running out of options!
Wait, actually.
If I was a frilled lizard,
I wouldn't have to deal with real people problems anymore.
But if I didn't want any problems,
I think I'd have a pretty easy life
if I was a living national treasure.
If I did become one, I wonder how much I would make...
And how do I become a living national treasure
in the first place?
Come to think of it, I'm not even sure what one is.
All right, enough crazy talk.
I need to come up with some realistic options.
What do I want to become? What do I want to do?
What to do...
No good. I've got nothing.
I just started high school,
so I guess I have a few years to think it over.
If I've still got nothing by then, that means...
College! Exams! And studying!
And I don't wanna study!
No, I can't think like that!
I just need a plan.
I have to figure out what I wanna do with my life.
Once I figure that out, everything will fall into place!
What do I wanna do?
Oh, hey, Mom!
Would you stop banging on the floor?!
Don't you know how late it is?
Well, I'm not too great with tough questions.
For now, I'll just do my homework.
Dammit! I still don't wanna do my homework!
Heya! I'm a frilled lizard!
I'm pretty tough to fold as origami!
It might take a few sheets
before you finally figure out how to make me!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 11!
You better look forward to it!