[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
[LANDLADY A]
Come on, you two.
When are you gonna get
around to paying rent?
You're up to 60,000 yen now!
[grunts]
[BIRD A]
I'm so sorry.
[LANDLADY A] I don't want
apologies! I want my money!
[cries]
[grunts]
Last time, you said you'd be
able to pay the rent in full
the next time
I came around for it.
Well, next time is now,
so cough it up!
[MOUSE A grunts]
[BIRD A gasps]
There's no use stone-walling
me in this situation.
I'm not leaving
without your rent.
[grunts]
[growls]
[grunting]
[growling]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[growls]
[BIRD A]
Um...
[BIRD A] This is all a
poor sparrow can spare.
[TV HOST A]
One: Meso-American Slider.
Two: Western Box Turtle.
Three: Red-Bellied,
Short-Necked Turtle.
It's two.
[TV HOST A]
The answer is... number three.
Great job, everyone.
Whatever.
[YUUKO'S MOM] Hey, what are you
still doing up at this hour?
Is your cold gone?
[YUUKO]
Mh-hm.
Then you should be good to
go back to school tomorrow.
Your tests are coming up soon.
Fine.
You've been out for
three whole days,
so you're gonna have to catch up
on your homework quickly.
See if you can borrow your
friends' notes from class.
I better not see you bring
home another failing score
like the last time.
You hear me?
Aw, come on, Mom! It's fine!
My finals don't even start
until, like... tomorrow!
I totally forgot!
Why didn't you remind me?
You were much too sick to study
anyway, so I let you rest.
[YUUKO]
Nuh-uh! I'd study in my sleep!
Would you really?
I wouldn't!
That's what I thought.
[YUUKO]
You didn't even bring it up,
I couldn't even try to study!
Would you have studied
if you'd known?
I guess not!
If you fail your exams,
I'll kill you.
[YUUKO]
You don't have to go that far!
[YUUKO] I'm super, ultra, great,
delicious, wonderfully screwed.
[YUUKO] Well, it looks
like I have no choice.
The next school day starts
in T-minus ten hours!
Luckily, tomorrow's tests are
just for English and music.
In that case, I'll focus
on English tonight.
'Kay, I just have to ignore
all of my natural lazy-person
instincts and concentrate.
I won't procrastinate!
So that I can live
on without regret.
So that I can laugh
in each coming day.
Even through all the
tears and sweat.
Even though obstacles
stand in my way.
I will never give up.
I want to keep a
smile on my face.
[YUUKO] I am like a ship
crossing the sea.
Sailing for the light
where I want to be.
On a straight track.
Breaking the chains
which hold me back.
Becoming my best self!
By Yuuko.
Perfect. I'm done...
...with a poem.
[MIO, YUUKO] Things we
think are freakin' cool!
It's nothing special.
Fuggedaboudit.
[MIO, YUUKO] The shy smile
of a local mechanic!
[YUUKO]
It's go time.
I dunno what's gonna
be on the test,
so I have to take it all in!
All right, vocab, come on!
Bring it!
Attempt: To make an effort.
Love: To earn my heart.
Always: We were always apart.
Confirmation: Your love is like.
Teleportation:
It crosses even time, so.
Cosmos: Sailing through
star and sky.
A midnight submarine:
I want to ride with you.
Forever, with you.
Forever, eternally.
Forever, until the end.
[YUUKO]
I'm done! With another poem!
Ugh! It's over! I'm screwed!
No matter how hard
I try, I can't study!
I'm so dead! My mom
is gonna kill me!
Why did I have to get over my
stupid cold today of all days?
Being sick is way better
than taking a test
that I'm doomed to fail!
If only I could be sick
for a just little longer!
[gasps]
[door opens]
I got it.
[YUUKO] My plan is
completely foolproof!
Yup.
[YUUKO]
If I wanna get out of the test,
I'll make myself sick again!
It stings! But I gotta
push through the pain!
My body is still weak
from beating my last cold,
so I bet I'll be running
a fever in no time.
[YUUKO] Come on, come on!
Just a little more.
[YUUKO]
If I can tough this out now,
then it'll all be
worth it in the end!
[YUUKO]
The path will open!
If I can get a fever,
then I'm all set!
I'll have some shaved
ice for good measure.
I'll blast the AC, too!
And go to sleep on
top of the covers!
[YUUKO sneezes]
[alarm rings]
Why do I have to be
so freakin' healthy?
[YUUKO'S MOM]
Yuuko! It's time to get up!
[YUUKO]
Last resort.
Thermometer... plus match...
...equals fever on-demand!
[YUUKO'S MOM]
Are you up yet?
You're going to school
today, right? Yuuko?
[YUUKO]
It burns! It burns!
[YUUKO'S MOM]
What are you doing?
Mom, I got a fever!
Guess I must've
gotten sick again.
[YUUKO'S MOM]
How bad is it?
Uh. Well, lemme see.
Huh? It's 88.8 degrees.
[YUUKO'S MOM]
What?
Now look at what you
did! You broke it!
[YUUKO] No, I didn't!
I got sick again, I swear!
[YUUKO'S MOM] You seem
perfectly healthy to me.
Yeah, It's probably because
there was something
in the water.
Thanks, man.
I had no idea that
today was the last day
to turn in our application.
One more day and the club
would've been a goner.
But even if you turn
in the form on time,
won't the club still
get shut down
for the lack of members?
Nah, I wouldn't
worry about that.
Tell ya what, how 'bout I bring
you some juice tomorrow
as a thanks.
You don't have to
do that. It's all good.
[DAIKU chuckles]
It's no problem at all! See ya!
Hey, I need to stop
and buy a juicer
and an apple orchard
on the way home.
[PILOT A]
Yes, sir.
[STUDENT B] Ah. So that's
the power of the Daiku Group.
[OURA]
No string left.
I won't be able to tie
together a straw doll
to put in the Principal's
locker if I don't have any.
And what's worse,
it looks like I don't even have
the straw to craft with,
nor do I have any
money to buy any.
My wife handles the
money, but she's gone.
We're all out of rice
and I'm hungry.
At times like these, a swig
of brandy would come in handy,
but my liver couldn't take it.
My favorite team lost,
and for whatever reason,
the cheeseburger
I ordered earlier
didn't have any cheese on it.
The visitor counter on
the home page of my website
hasn't budged at all,
and not a single
person logged on
to my usual online chat
group yesterday.
[car honks]
[OURA]
That empty chat room reminds me.
When I got on to the
bus the other day,
everyone else got off
and left me alone.
And that empty bus reminds me.
I went on a field trip
back in high school.
Time for bed.
[OURA]
And just a couple of minutes
after we turned
off the lights...
Who else is awake?
[OURA] I asked everyone,
but they were already asleep.
[song plays]
[OURA]
And speaking of sleep,
I haven't been getting
much of it lately.
Since I can't get any rest,
I ended up snacking
through the night,
and I've wound up
putting on some weight.
And speaking of food,
I got a present for my
birthday last month.
But it was just
a roll of bread.
[OURA]
This is no good!
All of this negative thinking
is getting me nowhere!
What I really need to do
is remember the
good things in life.
[doorbell rings]
[OURA]
Who could that be?
Yes?
Oh-ho!
Kimiko!
[KIMIKO] Mom is still away
on her trip, right?
I thought I'd come by
and make dinner.
I see. Well, thank you.
Hi, Grandpa!
Hello there, Mi.
Oh. Looks like you've
grown taller, huh?
[MITSUO chuckles]
[OURA]
Just what I needed.
I'll spend some time
with my grandson,
who hasn't a care in the world.
[MITSUO]
Guess what, Grandpa?
[OURA]
Hm?
I made a dumpling when
I was at the park earlier.
You can have it if you want!
That so?
[MITSUO] You're hungry,
so you should eat it!
How sweet.
It's real chocolate,
so you're gonna like it!
Oh, can I really?
Well, thank you.
[KIMIKO chuckles]
[KIMIKO]
What's with the water works?
I guess you've always
been the sensitive type.
'Kay, I'll be in the
kitchen if you need me.
Okay.
[OURA]
That's right.
There's no point in focusing
on all of the negative
things in life.
[MITSUO] I made it with love
just for you, grandpa!
Come on, hurry up!
Eat the dumpling!
It's yummy, I promise!
Well, uh, this is...
Eat it! What are
you waiting for?
You should eat it! It's tasty!
[OURA]
I'm sure.
Somehow, happiness tastes
just about as good as dirt.
[thud]
[MITSUO]
Hey, Mom? Grandpa fell down.
Your order. Thanks for waiting.
[CUSTOMER C gasps]
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
There is nothing--
nothing greater than peace.
[SAKAMOTO]
Trying to kill me?
[HAKASE]
It's finished!
[SAKAMOTO]
What's up?
[gasps]
Super-duper glue!
[SAKAMOTO]
That is quite large.
[HAKASE]
Because it's super-duper.
[HAKASE chuckles]
[HAKASE] I'm gonna spread
this so Nano and Sakamoto
will get here stuck when
they least expect it.
[SAKAMOTO] What kind of prank
are you tryin' to pull now?
You're being so obvious
no one is gonna fall for your--
[SAKAMOTO yelps]
Gotcha!
[SAKAMOTO]
You got me in what?
Hey! Get this stuff off of me!
I've got things to do, ya know!
[HAKASE giggles]
[HAKASE]
It'll only come off with water.
[SAKAMOTO] Then go get some
water and set me free!
Hold on, it's snack time.
[SAKAMOTO]
Hey!
Since it's snack time,
I need to go to the kitchen,
so see ya for now.
[SAKAMOTO]
No!
[gasps]
My feet. Hang on.
Oh, no. Uh.
[SAKAMOTO]
Hey.
Do something. This sucks.
[HAKASE]
Heh. You look like a bug
who got stuck in a glue trap.
[SAKAMOTO]
What are you laughing at?
You're stuck in here, too!
Uh. Oh, that's right.
[laughs]
[SAKAMOTO]
Serves you right!
That's some karma for ya!
[HAKASE]
That's weird. I-I can't get out.
[SAKAMOTO] It's your own fault
for being such a troublemaker.
I've fallen and I can't get up.
Hang on. Where'd Sakamoto go?
[HAKASE]
Kitty-kitty? Kitty-kitty?
There you are!
[SAKAMOTO grunting]
This won't come off
without water.
I won't be able to eat
snacks if I'm stuck here.
What if I'm stuck to the floor
for a really long time
and get super hungry?
I won't be able
to eat my snacks.
Am I'm gonna starve?
I don't wanna become a skeleton.
[SAKAMOTO]
I'm actually dying here.
[NANO]
Hello! I'm back!
It's Nano!
I'm happy to be home.
It's so hot out there and--
What happened?
How'd you end up like that?
Well, I put down this glue!
Just like that! And it
got all sticky-like!
But then I tripped and fell,
and got stuck in it, and now
I need water, and I need...
Water?
[HAKASE]
That's right!
You should really get up
off the floor first.
And then we should get this
mess cleaned up before--
[HAKASE yelps]
Huh? What is this stuff?
Hey! Uh.
How did he--? Here, I'll, uh--
[NANO gasps]
Oh, no! My hand came off!
[HAKASE laughing]
I don't understand
what's happening!
[laughing]
[NANO whines]
[NANO]
Oh, no! My other hand!
President.
So this is the true power
of the Daiku Group.
[humming]
Ha. Well, that sure was a
lovely rainbow we just saw.
Hey! Guess who!
Well, is it Hakase?
Yay, that's correct!
Good job. How'd you know?
I mean, it's kinda obvious.
No one else lives here, so...
[HAKASE] Okay! Now it's
your turn to play, Nano!
[NANO]
Huh? All right then.
Hey! Guess who!
You! Nano!
[SAKAMOTO gasps]
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome household.
[HAKASE]
Hey, Nano! I was right, right?
[NANO]
Uh, yeah. You were.
[HAKASE]
Great! I get to go again now!
So turn around!
[NANO]
Sure.
[gasps]
[YUUKO]
This is bad. So bad.
Really bad!
I'm still stuck on the
first stupid question!
What is this thing?
It looks like some sort of
low-level monster or something.
But how do I describe
that in one word?
[YUUKO]
Wait, I've seen this. But where?
I think I asked Ms. Sakurai
about it before, but when?
Let's see.
[YUUKO]
What is this supposed to be?
No, I'm not asking
about the answer.
I'm wondering if
you were the one
who drew this low-level-
looking monster.
[YUUKO] That's it! I did
ask about this dude!
[YUUKO groans]
[YUUKO]
I don't remember what she said!
Just calm down!
I need to breathe.
If I panic, I won't be
able to think straight!
All right, focus.
What is this thing doing?
Flying? Was that it?
No, it can't be.
This little guy
is so distracting!
Why can't I stop focusing
on this monster?
Wait, monster?
This isn't just testing
my language skills.
It's testing my sanity.
But this is the best I can do,
so I should just move on.
So what's next?
[screams]
[YUUKO] It's the same monster
swinging a tennis racket!
Which means the first answer
is definitely not monster.
Why is this thing torturing me?
I'll just erase my first
answer and start over.
[YUUKO]
Where is my eraser?
[YUUKO] Every dang thing
in my stupid life sucks!
What do I do now?
This is so bad!
[YUUKO] Do I just have to
live with my mistakes?
[gasps]
[YUUKO]
Mai! You saved me!
I'm so glad we're
friends! Best friends!
[YUUKO]
A sand eraser?
I can't use this!
It'll rip my paper!
That defeats the purpose!
I don't have time
to worry about that!
I need to see if Mai has a--
She went to sleep!
Uh. All right,
ten minutes remaining!
[YUUKO]
My time! It's ticking away!
Come on, I gotta calm down.
That's right.
I have to relax...
and just clear my mind.
Purge all thought. Be free.
[bell rings]
Okay. And time's up!
[YUUKO]
No!
It's raining.
[YUUKO]
Only in my heart.
Good morning, sir!
Yes, good morning!
[STUDENT C] No way!
I just got a love letter!
[STUDENT D]
Are you for real? Who sent it?
[STUDENT C] It says it's
from Tanaka in Class Four!
[STUDENT D]
Come on! Open it already!
[STUDENT C]
Don't rush me!
[wheezing]
[DIRT]
I'm a dirt ball.
[IRON BALL]
I'm an iron ball!
[DIRT] I'd tell you a joke,
but none of mine are clean.
[IRON BALL] And I shall
strike when the iron is hot!
Clang-clang!
[DIRT] The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 12.
[IRON BALL]
Look forward to it!