[KOUJIROU snoring]
[FE] Was Sasahara was
actually asleep in there?
[WEBOSHII]
Uh, yeah, totally.
Didn't you see him? He was
100 percent taking a nap.
Ooh, you should go
wake him up, Misato.
Huh?
He probably isn't
aware that we're
changing classrooms right now,
so you should let him know.
That's not my responsibility!
Why should I care?
Come on, don't be like that.
He's your friend, isn't he?
It's not a big deal.
[FE]
And besides,
you'll probably have
the room to yourselves
if you're feelin' feisty.
Huh? What? No way!
Well, have fun, you two!
Tell us the details later!
No! You--! [groans]
Why do I have to be stuck
with babysitting that idiot?
Just because we've known
each other forever.
You should just confess your
feelings to him already!
[gasps]
[KOUJIROU snoring]
[MISATO gasps, sighs]
Sasahara!
We're changing classrooms,
so would you get up?
We gotta go!
Uh--it's you.
Miss Tachibana.
[gasps]
Just go and grab whatever
you need for the next class.
[KOUJIROU]
Of course.
I only intended to rest
my eyes for a moment,
but it seems as though I must
have been lulled to sleep.
I don't give a crap
about any of that!
Get your stuff before
people get the wrong idea.
Wrong idea? How so?
[gasps] Just forget it!
--[thud]
--[gasps]
I'm so sorry!
I mean, I'm not
sorry for doing it,
I'm sorry it that
happened, I mean.
Who puts their glasses
on a desk anyway?
[KOUJIROU]
Misato Tachibana.
Look. Your hand is bleeding.
[MISATO gasps]
You don't have to act
all nice, y'know.
I broke your glasses,
so you have every right
to be angry with me.
Why?
Glasses feel no pain
when they're broken.
You're the one who's hurting.
[MISATO gasps]
Yeah, no duh!
My hand's bleeding!
That much is obvious!
Fortunately for us,
one of the lenses is still
in its rightful place.
As long as the lens hangs on
to the glasses, so will I.
[gasps]
[MISATO] It's like the
glasses somehow knew...
[MISATO]
...and let go.
[gasps]
Follow me.
[KOUJIROU]
You really don't--
[MISATO]
I know!
But I have to take
responsibility.
It's my fault!
[KOUJIROU gasps]
[MALE STUDENT 25A]
You get what I'm saying?
It was totally lame, right?
That's why, uh...
[MALE STUDENT 25B gasps]
Yeah, totally.
And then I said--uh...
[FEMALE STUDENT 25B gasps]
[MISATO]
Oh, man, everyone is staring!
I could die. I'm dying!
I am literally dead right now.
But I have to do this.
Sasahara's probably blind
without his glasses,
so I have to be his eyes.
It's fine. No big deal.
His glasses are broken,
so this isn't weird, right?
Totally, 100 percent
understandable.
Yeah! I'm helping out
a person in need!
Like a seeing-eye dog.
An embarrassed,
dying, seeing-eye dog.
[KOUJIROU]
Excuse me, Miss Tachibana.
Uh, yeah?
Before we reach the classroom,
I'd like to take a visit
to the facilities.
Wait! So... the bathroom?
The boy's bathroom?
[KOUJIROU]
Naturally.
[MISATO] This'll be
harder than I thought!
[MISATO]
But I can't back down now.
I have to do this for him.
For us!
Fine! I'll go in with you!
But why?
[MISATO] Because your glasses
are broken, aren't they?
They are.
[MISATO] Come on! Don't make
me spell it out for you!
Your glasses are broken!
So, uh... since it was my fault,
I'm gonna be your
eyes for today.
Oh. These are just for style.
[MIO, YUUKO panting]
Don't get the wrong idea!
I wasn't holding your arm
because I wanted to or anything!
There was a bug on your sleeve
and I was just trying to
squish it very slowly.
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
What beautiful weather today.
[SAKAMOTO]
Uh--
Huh?
[NANO whimpering]
[TAKASAKI]
Uh--! So, uh,
I know this spicy curry
place in Kamakura!
[IZUMI]
Oh! That's nice!
How spicy do you like
your food, Ms. Sakurai?
Oh? Well, uh...
No spice at all.
Same! What a coincidence!
[YUUKO gasps]
Uh...
So, um... our next class.
We're going to be late.
[MIO]
Wait, Mio!
The classroom is in
the other direction!
[MIO]
The other direction.
Try to think of it this way!
Life is just like baseball,
and sometimes you
end up striking out!
But you can't stop
playing the game!
[MIO] Sometimes you
end up striking out.
Just like baseball.
[YUUKO]
Let's not jump to conclusions!
We don't even know if those two
are actually a thing or not!
Back me up on this, Nano!
[NANO]
Huh? Oh. Yeah!
What she said!
[MIO]
But, Koujirou...
He couldn't.
[MIO]
He wouldn't.
He did.
[YUUKO] Anyway, we should
get going. Come on, Mio.
[MIO sobbing]
--[YUUKO] Mio!
--[NANO] Come back!
[YUUKO] Nano! You get to
class and buy us some time!
I'll take care of her!
Right!
[YUUKO grunts]
Mio, wait!
[YUUKO]
Mio! That's a window!
Mio!
[YUUKO]
--[MIO sobbing]
--[YUUKO] Mio, wait!
[YUUKO]
Mio!
Mi-oh!
--[MIO panting]
--Mio!
--[MAN 25A] Huh?
[YUUKO gasps]
[YUUKO]
Uh! Mio?
[CROWD gasping]
Hey! Mio?
[YUUKO]
Mio! Mio!
--Say cheese!
--[YUUKO] Wait, Mio!
Mio!
[YUUKO]
This is my stop.
Mio!
Mio! Watch out!
Look, Mio!
[YUUKO screaming]
[YUUKO]
Mio!
Mio, stop!
Mio! Mio!
Maa fell in the river!
Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio!
Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio!
[MIO grunting]
[MIO panting]
[MIO]
Dammit all!
[YUUKO]
Mi-o-my!
[MAA gasping]
[YUUKO]
Dios Mio !
[MIO, MAA panting]
Thank you.
[YUUKO]
Hey, Mio!
I thought I lost you back there!
[panting]
I'm fine.
I just need to breathe.
Well, that's good.
[POLICEMAN 16A]
Where is he?
This way! [gasps]
There you are, Maa!
[MAA]
Osamu!
Thank goodness you're safe!
You all right?
[MAA]
Yeah, I think so.
If this lady didn't save me,
I'd be in big trouble.
Wait! You again?
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL]
From before!
[POLICEMAN 16A]
I hope the two of you are aware
that interfering with
official police business
is a criminal offense!
But I didn't do anything!
Under normal circumstances,
I would report this
directly to your school.
But in this case, I suppose I
can overlook it just this once.
Do you mean it?
[GENTLEMAN 2A]
Ah, there you are!
I've finally caught up to you
and your little pigtails.
[pants] I saw your
shadow boxing.
And you have a true gift.
Uh...
[GENTLEMAN 2A]
What about it?
With your talents...
[GENTLEMAN 2A] ...you could
rule the boxing world.
[OLD WOMAN 25A]
Help! Help! He stole my bag!
[THIEF 25A]
Don't think badly of me!
Well! Duty calls!
Come to the station later
and you'll get a
commendation for your help!
[MAA]
Here, lady. This is for you.
[MIO gasps]
Thanks.
--[MAA] Osamu, that okay?
--[OSAMU] Yeah!
[GENTLEMAN 2A]
Whenever you're ready,
please visit me at my gym,
and then your journey can begin.
[YUUKO] Oh, no! Mio,
you lost your English textbook
during all that madness!
[giggling]
[laughing]
Mio?
[MIO]
Rejected before I could confess.
Rescued a child while running
from my own troubles.
Received an award and a kite.
Got scouted by a boxing coach.
In a way, life really
is just like baseball.
[MIO]
I have to keep playing the game.
Huh?
Isn't that what you
told me before?
Who knows what'll happen.
So keep going.
That right?
[YUUKO]
Huh? What's right?
[MIO]
You get it.
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
I just realized
that daydreaming
is totally free.
[NAKAMURA] Damn. I completely
lost track of her.
[NAKAMURA]
I was hot on her trail
when she was running
around the school,
but I took my eyes
off her for a moment,
and she suddenly slipped away!
Huh?
[NAKAMURA] A remarkable
and surprising feature!
I must know more about your
advanced functionalities,
Nano Shinonome!
[NAKAMURA] Now then,
I've traveled this far.
Perhaps I should try
locating her home.
Hmm, on second thought, it might
be best to tread carefully.
I'll continue my pursuit
for knowledge tomorrow
and retreat for the time being.
[NAKAMURA]
It's hiding in plain sight!
I've discovered this house
completely by chance. Finally!
My first stroke of luck
since I started this mission!
No, this more than mere luck!
This is more like, um,
what's the word...
It's like, uh...
I can't think of it!
I'm too caught up in
the thrill of the moment!
To think, the genius
who built her
could be in that very building!
Nano's blueprints could be mine
to study her every detail!
For science!
What is this strange
pounding in my chest?
It's like a hootenanny!
Like former professional
wrestler cowboy Bill Watts
is beating on my heart himself!
If this is indeed the
house of her creator,
then there's no telling what
sort of traps there may be.
If I am to infiltrate
this place,
I must be extremely cautious
and pay close attention
to my surroundings.
Can I help you, lady?
[NAKAMURA]
I'm compromised!
Oh, no!
I've been spotted by the
home's surveillance robot!
The build quality looks
lower than Nano's,
but he's likely made with the
same advanced technology.
If it determines
that I'm a threat,
he'll undoubtedly dispose of me!
I have no choice!
I must show that I mean no harm!
What are you doing
on the ground?
[NAKAMURA]
Compromised again!
So, I heard that goat of yours
carried an injured old lady
to the hospital last week.
Yes, he did.
Then the reason you bring
a goat is because it's
a service animal for
emergency situations like that?
[KOUJIROU chuckles]
Silly.
[TOMIOKA sighs]
Yeah. Well, I'm not the
one who rides a goat.
[NANO]
Here you are.
[NAKAMURA] I can't believe
they got the jump on me.
I was trying to infiltrate
the Shinonome home,
but a warm, hospitable welcome
was not what I had in mind.
However, I can see
through this ruse.
I'm on to their tricks.
For example, this tea.
I'm certain it contains
some sort of drug
that will erase my memory
the moment I drink it.
And this room may seem ordinary,
but I'm sure I'm being watched.
[gasps] What is that?
It has a terrifyingly
concerning aura.
Such random placement.
And those painted-on
sunglasses can't fool me!
I can't see its eyes, but I can
certainly feel their gaze!
I can't make a single wrong
move. It's all-seeing!
What's wrong, Ms. Nakamura?
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Absolutely nothing!
My apologies!
[NAKAMURA]
I drank it all.
I'm a fool.
But if this does wipe my memory,
then I might as well
make a stand!
[NAKAMURA] I'll be
completely honest with you.
Huh? Sure, go ahead.
I came to your home today
to find out everything
I can about you!
Huh?
Wha?
I want to see what you're
really like underneath it all!
--[NANO gasps]
--So, please!
Uh, well, I mean, you're
free to like what you like
and pursue what
you please, but, uh--
I appreciate it,
but I just don't think
any romantic involvement
between the two of us
would be the most
appropriate thing right now!
[gasps] You idiot!
You misunderstand my words!
You can't just say
things like that to me
out of nowhere, you know!
[NANO] Ah, I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to!
When I said that I wanted to see
what you're like underneath--
[HAKASE]
Nano?
--Hakase!
--[NAKAMURA] Huh?
[NAKAMURA]
A child?
It couldn't be her child.
Of course not.
She's a robot after all!
But that garb.
It's that of an intellectual.
Could she be Nano's creator?
So, this child is not
the child at all,
but maybe Nano is
the child? Yes?
There's no way someone so
young could create Nano.
Hello, you can call me Hakase.
Oh, and I created Nano.
[NAKAMURA]
Shoulder block!
[NANO gasps]
Hakase!
[NAKAMURA]
So it's true.
This child is Nano's creator.
--[SAKAMOTO] Hey!
--[NAKAMURA gasps]
[SAKAMOTO] Could you
get me out of this thing?
I'm tired of all of your pranks!
[NAKAMURA gasping]
[NAKAMURA]
A homunculus!
The surveillance robot,
and the daruma weapon,
and the child creator, and Nano
Shinonome, and the homunculus!
I admit that I was
a fool to think that
I was even remotely prepared to
try and infiltrate this home.
But I never could have
seen any of this coming!
I must find a chance
to strategically retreat
and reformulate my plans.
But...
Knowing that thing is watching
has me paralyzed in fear.
I couldn't make an attempt
to leave even if I tried!
If I suddenly state out of
nowhere that I have to go home--
[NAKAMURA gasps]
[NAKAMURA]
I have no other options.
[HAKASE, NANO gasp]
Where's the bathroom?
I must pee.
Uh, okay.
I'll show you where to go--
[NAKAMURA]
No need!
If you can give
me the directions,
I can find it on my own.
[NAKAMURA chuckles] I've
completely outwitted you again,
Nano Shinonome.
My plan worked perfectly.
Because of course it did.
I knew how you'd respond.
You see, I capitalized
on your weakness.
That's right.
Your kindness leaves you
gullible and far too trusting!
And when I return
to this deathtrap
you call your humble abode,
I shall turn the
tables on you yet.
Just you wait.
As long as I have this
big brain of mine,
you'll be completely
at my mercy!
Eventually!
Oh. Are you leaving?
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Crap!
Uh, well, you see,
I was just asked to mow the
grass on the lawn outside and--
[NAKAMURA gasps]
What the--?
[BISCUIT #2]
Hang on! Don't move!
I'll get help!
No! Wait! Don't go!
[NAKAMURA]
Oh, no! They're onto me!
They're going to see me out here
and realize that I lied to
them and tried to escape!
Dammit, what is this stuff?
It's robbing me of
my movement, my freedom!
She's over here!
Huh? But the bathroom's
the other direction.
[NANO gasps]
What is this thing?
Right! Hakase!
Your special glue comes off
with water, doesn't it?
[NAKAMURA] If they capture me
here, then I'll be done for!
But my studies! My science!
[NAKAMURA gasps]
[NAKAMURA]
Oh, no!
I must find a way to get
out of this literal mess!
Curse you, clever bastards
of the Shinonome Lab!
[NANO]
Water!
[NAKAMURA]
Somebody help.
Anybody!
Get me out of here!
[MONK 25A groans]
[MIO]
Oh, I actually have that one.
[ANNAKA] Really? Do you
think I could borrow it?
Yeah, sure. I can
bring it tomorrow.
[NANO] "Who knows what'll
happen" and "that's baseball"?
Is that all she said?
[YUUKO] Yeah. And she
was acting all happy
and laughing and stuff.
[NANO] Maybe she was
trying to be strong
and laugh through the pain.
Getting indirectly rejected
by the guy you like
isn't something you
just "get over."
[YUUKO] Well, she doesn't not
look like she's not unhappy.
[NANO]
Wait, run that by me again?
Yuuko, you forgot your
homework again, didn't you?
No! Don't be ridiculous!
But wait, I actually
did forget, so yeah.
Make up your mind!
You'll find out
after the commercial!
Huh?
Wow! That was so
random and funny!
Don't you think so?
Fleming?
Wait, rap?
[ANNAKA]
Oh, and Mio.
There's something else
I gotta ask you.
Okay.
What's up?
Hey, Yuuko. You know
her the best, right?
Can you think of anything
that might help cheer her up?
[MIO]
I wonder where they all went.
And here I was hoping we could
go out and grab some food
after we were done with class.
[MIO gasps]
What are you guys doing?
[MAI, NANO, YUUKO]
Congratulations, young lady!
[YUUKO]
Please take a spin!
[MIO]
I know it's Yuuko. Cut the act.
[YUUKO]
Yuu-who?
Never heard of her!
[MIO]
You're so obvious.
I see Nano's key poking out.
[NANO] It's not like this is
a robotic key or anything!
[YUUKO] Uh, anyways, everyone
who passes through here
has to take a crack
at the lottery!
So, step right up!
But why?
I don't really know
what you guys are doing.
Well whatever.
[YUUKO] Congratulations,
we have a winner!
How? I don't get it.
[YUUKO]
And here's your special prize!
What makes it special?
[YUUKO]
Just open it and find out!
'Kay?
Your weird practical jokes are
getting harder and
harder to understand,
you know that, Yuuko? Uh--
[gasps]
[YUUKO] Wonderful!
Now please move along!
[NANO]
Thank you for coming!
[MAI]
Bonus prize.
Freshly carved.
Oh, thanks a lot.
[YUUKO, NANO gasp]
[MIO]
This reminds me.
There was something that
Koujirou said a while back.
What was it?
[MIO] Something about our
ordinary lives passing us by.
And how it may actually be a
series of wonderful miracles.
I think... no, I know...
all of that is true.
[MIO]
All right!
I'm gonna go home
and draw some manga!
How'd this happen?
It's all your fault
we got lost out here!
Apologies. I'll find
directions on my "mobile."
Why are you saying
that all weird?
Just talk like a normal person!
[KOUJIROU laughs]
[MISATO]
Wait! Hey!
Are you watching TV on there?
Perhaps you should
consume media content
on your "mobile" as well.
[MISATO gasps]
My phone isn't that fancy!
[NANO'S KEY]
I'm Nano's key!
Sometimes I spin!
And sometimes I don't.
Sometimes I even get pulled out!
That's my ordinary life!
And the next My Ordinary Life
is the last one!
Look forward to it!