Lunch time, so I'm out of the woods!
I can't believe you got away with
not doing your homework again.
It's about time that I had some good luck, Mio.
I was getting tired of having to
stand out in the hallway every day.
Maybe things are looking up for me.
Just do your homework.
Y'know what'd be great?
You getting me a juice to celebrate my luck!
Huh?
Young lady. We need to have a little chat
about your missing assignments,
so please come to the faculty room immediately.
Okay.
Maybe I should get her a juice.
Hey! I'm over here!
Oh, hey! I'm sorry.
Were you waiting long?
Not at all!
I actually just got here myself.
Sis sure is being extra loud with her friends tonight.
'Kay, so, I gotta know.
How are "things"?
--Hm? --How's what now?
Don't you be shy!
Come on!
I'm talkin' about you and Koujirou's love life.
Why would I even think about
marrying and spending my life with that weirdo?
What? I never mentioned that!
And children?
You can forget it!
I hear ya loud and clear!
You, Koujirou, and his goat
already have a long and happy life planned out together!
No, we don't.
So, what's been going on with you, Weboshii?
Huh? Who, me?
Nothing you need to know about.
Aww, hey, you can tell me!
Is there somebody you have your eye on?
Uh-huh.
Just spit it out!
I wanna know!
Stop it, stop it!
Okay! I'll tell you...
I'm not stopping till you say who it is!
All right! As soon as you let me go!
You better speak up right now, or else!
Ow!
I already said I'd tell you!
Sorry. I was having so much
fun, I guess I got carried away.
So? Give us the juicy details!
I wanna know more about this guy you like!
Hmm. I wouldn't say that I like him, not yet anyway.
Sure, I'm interested, but I don't even know his name.
He's that one cool guy with the mohawk.
--Ahh. --It's that guy.
Oh, so you know who I'm talking about, then?
Everybody knows about him.
He's pretty popular with that crazy hairdo of his.
Of course we'd know him.
But why are you interested in him of all people, Weboshii?
Hmm.
I guess he kinda...
...gives off a bad-boy vibe.
I dunno, there's something about the dangerous type.
He totally seems like one of those, right?
Yeah, definitely.
And his mohawk is like a bad-boy beacon!
Get this. I saw him the other day,
and he was being a good, upstanding member of society.
Yeah, okay!
The only thing that's upstanding is his hair!
I'm serious. I know what I saw.
He was watering the school's flowers.
What? Get outta here!
Oh, yeah, and then, he, like,
even fed the plants with this fertilizer stuff.
Oh, wow!
I never thought he'd be so sweet!
You can't judge a book by its cover, huh?
Yeah, you got that right.
I guess he isn't a punk after all.
And I think I might actually
like him more now that I know.
Yeah I get what you mean.
I prefer it when guys are nice, too.
So does that mean there's
someone you've got the hots for right now?
What, me? Well, I, uh...
Sasahara's that way.
Here you are.
I saw him feeding his goat this one time in the
pouring rain and I thought that was pretty nice.
Yeah, I get it!
That does sound pretty nice. Mm-hmm, mm-hmm!
I see why you like him.
What? I never said I liked him or anything
just because he's nice.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm! So anyway!
Tell us who you're after!
Huh? What do you mean?
If you like someone, then tell us who it is.
Um, I can't think of anyone in particular
that I'm interested in.
I guess I'm just not into weirdos like you guys are.
Helvetica Standard.
--Begin! --Seiya!
Here I come!
Soiya!
One point!
Ow! Man, that hurts.
Hang on a sec. Here.
Thanks, I really appreciate it--
What's wrong? Lemme see your hand.
Huh?
It's finally my day off,
but since I have so many errands to run,
this will end up being just as busy as a regular work day.
Oh, well. At least it's peaceful.
I guess that's enough.
It looks like this'll be another
boring day for me, then, huh?
Hello there.
Hm?
Casual clothes?
This is what she looks like outside of work?
Are you out shopping as well, Mr. Takasaki?
And those pigtails!
Bumping into Sakurai like this on a weekend?
It's almost as if we're more than just colleagues.
I'm so happy.
This is the best day ever.
Oh, no, are you okay?
You're not feeling ill, are you?
Don't worry about me!
I'm surprised to see you here, that's all!
Oh! Could you be out shopping today, too, Ms. Sakurai?
Yes! There's a great sale on green onions today,
so I figured I'd go out and pick some up.
Green onions, huh?
Well, if you ever find yourself needing bamboo sprouts,
just give me a shout and I'll get you some!
Uh, you have extra bamboo sprouts?
Well, I kind of have...
You know, come to think of it...
Really, you do?
That sounds wonderful!
Bumping into her like this on the weekend...
It feels like it was meant to be.
Almost as if fate brought us together.
This wasn't some chance encounter. It was destiny.
I never believed in this kind of stuff before,
but I think I get it now.
I wish I were a green onion!
You sure you're okay?
It kind of looks like you're in pain, so...
...maybe we should sit down.
Don't worry about me!
I'm doing completely fine, 100 percent fine!
I wouldn't want you to trouble
yourself with something like--
...maybe we should sit down.
With something like...
This is the best.
I hope it never ends.
I know! I have a great idea, Ms. Sakurai!
There's a park a few blocks down,
so why don't we go down there and sit down?
Uh, okay!
Oh, man.
I can't believe this is actually happening right now.
Hang on!
Could this be... considered a date?!
Why is she here?
Actually, you know what? I'm fine!
So maybe we should just turn around.
A student, here? Now?
I can't have her seeing us together.
Uh... Hey! What are you two doing over there?
D-Don't be silly!
This is just a completely casual meeting between adults.
And, uh, that's it!
Fancy seeing you here!
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you two were on a secret date or something.
If you think it's a secret, why would you say it out loud?
Aw, what's the big deal?
You guys look like you're having fun!
You turd.
Uh--hm?
I hope you're having a fine morning today, Ms. Sakurai.
Huh?
Look, it's the two love birds!
Look at 'em blush!
Ooh!
That's enough!
No teasing the teachers!
Those darn kids always take things too far.
I'm sorry about all this.
I hope it didn't cause you too much trouble.
It didn't.
But, um...
I, um, thought it was kinda cute.
That's it! Okay! Let's do this!
What's wrong with me?
It would never work out so perfectly like that!
I gotta get outta here!
What's going on?
Nothing!
Why does it look like you're
hiding something, Mr. Takasaki?
Well, it's been a lovely coincidence
seeing you here, Ms. Sakurai!
And wouldn't ya know it, there's a student here, too!
What are the chances of seeing two people
from the school in the exact same place!
Hm? What was your name?
It's Aioi, isn't that right?
Just kidding! Of course I'd remember!
Uh--
Well! In any case!
I've got places to go and people to see,
so if you'll excuse me, I'm gonna hit the 'ol dusty trail!
Maybe... I should pick up some green onions.
Sorry for calling you out like this.
You sleep okay last night?
I did, but... I had the most peculiar dream.
Oh, really? What happened?
Well, um... we were standing here kissing.
What if I made that dream a reality?
Hey! Uh, Hakase!
Let's go get you some more snacks!
Do you really have those kinds of feelings for me?
Save your questions for after.
Oh, my! Sir!
After one whole month of investigating,
I've determined that Nano Shinonome
visits the supermarket in this district every Saturday.
If my calculations are correct, she'll be arriving soon.
And once she does, I'll be right behind her.
When I find my opening,
I'll call upon my trusty friend, Mr. Short Circuit,
once again to assist me in this abduction.
For science!
It's the perfect plan!
Today shall be the day I study you, Miss Shinonome!
Or not!
Why isn't she showing up?
Could it be that she doesn't
come to the supermarket every week?
Maybe my calculations were off.
No. I can't give up now.
I've already waited this long,
so I can't let it be for nothing!
Hmm.
I knew it! So it is you, Ms. Nakamura.
Fancy seeing you here.
Likewise, you walking pair of sideburns!
Uh, hello there.
I hardly recognized you
without your usual lab coat on.
I don't have time for this
pointless small talk right now.
If I don't focus,
Nano Shinonome might slip through my fingers
without me even noticing her.
I never woulda guessed that your street clothes
would be so boy-ish.
I'm surprised.
It looks pretty cute on you.
Um, well, no, actually, this is just my, uh...
I'm so used to you being all
serious with that lab coat on,
so seeing you like this makes you seem cuter, I guess.
I'll have to retreat for today!
Hang on, you forgot your science thingy!
So then,
have you given any thought to what you might
want to do in the future at all, Miss Minakami?
I have thought about it.
Uh... So, are you planning on finding a job?
Then... are you... looking into higher education?
Uh... 'Kay that means...
I think I get it.
Hey, you find it yet?
It's no good.
We can't find the cube.
I thought we stored that thing
somewhere safe.
How could it just disappear?
Well, look on the bright side.
There's gonna be a huge cash reward
for whoever finds the dang thing.
I'd say that's worth all the trouble
we're going through.
Ha, yeah!
If we can find one, then we can find the other.
Better keep looking.
If I could just get my hands on that cube.
I wonder if that would help me
get in the King's good graces.
Hey, uh, who's that?
Over there?
Huh?
My wooden cube.
Give it back.
Hey, now.
What seems to be the big problem here, little girl?
How did you manage to get on this ship?
Don't tell me.
You're some kind of stowaway?
Do you know how we punish kids for doing that?
We throw them straight into prison.
Ten years minimum.
And the worst part is, I'd be your warden!
That what you want?
No, 22!
Damn it! You're gonna pay!
Hold it. I can handle this.
I got careless for a split second there.
But I've got this under control now, trust me.
I gotta say.
You sure do pack quite a powerful punch
for such a tiny girl.
Now then.
This has been fun,
but it's time you started talk--
Is he okay?
Negative. He's dead.
She's a monster!
The stowaway isn't gonna stop
until she gets the wooden cube!
Let's charge at her together!
We've got her outnumbered.
Hmm.
There's no reason to panic,
now that I'm here, so everybody can settle down.
Officer!
Relax. Just sit back and watch how it's done.
In this situation,
the Officer might actually be our only hope.
Hmm. So, she's on a solo mission
to claim the wooden cube.
Undoubtedly a highly-skilled
agent sent by an unknown enemy.
All that skill and power could be quite useful, though,
if we can convince her to switch over to our side.
Fortunately, I am in possession of the other wooden cube.
It's what she wants,
so it makes the perfect bargaining chip,
and we should be able to come to an agreement.
I just happen to have the cube you're looking for,
so what do you say we make a trade?
We could strike a promising deal--
Ooh!
Officer!
He's dead, too!
This is not good!
She took down the Officer like it was nothing!
We'll show you!
We're not gonna let you out of here alive!
This is bad! Really, really bad!
By definition, that means it's not good.
What does that mean, Scholar?
How bad is "really, really bad"?
If you would all stop yelling at me for a moment
and observe the intruder's head,
you'll notice that she has a wooden cube in her hair.
And if you look on the other side of her head,
there's another wooden cube.
Meaning that she has a total of two wooden cubes!
Which means that she has both
wooden cubes in her possession!
But even if she has
both the cubes,
we should be fine as long as she doesn't know
how to summon the ancient weapon.
That's right! We can still win if--
Shut up and listen to me!
It says here in the Hell Encyclopedia,
that whoever possesses both of the wooden cubes
will be bestowed with the unstoppable power
of the ancient weapon!
In other words,
it means that whoever possesses both of the wooden cubes
will be bestowed with the unstoppable power
of the ancient weapon.
What does that mean?
Explain that once more, please!
Yeah, I didn't get it the first time!
In other--
There's no time to explain!
It is over!
If we try to fight here, not only will we be doomed,
but the entire world along with us!
Don't you dare back down!
Never run from you fears!
Conquer them!
It's the Captain!
Captain!
All right!
Listen. Trying to attack her
head-on one at a time will only guarantee your demise.
It would be futile.
However! The enemy is but one lone girl!
So we have the advantage of numbers on our side!
We must work together as a complete unit
to rush in and take those wooden cubes from her
no matter the cost!
I'll take point and lead the vanguard!
Attack!
Captain!
Forget about me! Carry on!
But, we can't just--
You piddling maggot!
I don't remember training a pathetic,
cowardly soldier like you!
It's all over.
The Officer is gone.
The Captain is stuck in a hole.
What hope do we have left now?
We're a team.
And we still have each other.
One for all... and all for one!
Captain, no!
It's been 12 long years since I joined this squad.
Over a decade of my life gone in a flash,
because of this girl.
It can't be over.
I'm not done yet.
It won't end like this!
We're doomed!
Please, no!
I don't wanna die here!
Huh?
I'll go stand in the hallway.
That's so obvious!
Whatever.
I've got nothing else to do right now,
so I might as well indulge the little brat.
Making something a waste of time
is a special talent indeed.
Hmm.
Oh, you have bed-head.
It's actually pretty cute on you.
It looks pretty cute on you.
What the hell am I doing?
What's wrong with me?
I'm finished now!
The bath is all yours whenever you--
I'm a Love Umbrella.
If you need a matchmaker, I've got you covered!
Write your name on one side,
and your special someone on the other.
Oh? You don't have one?
Then for a sad sap like you,
the next My Ordinary Life is Episode 22.
Look forward to it!