[SUDO]
This is bad. We're screwed!
(Crash)
[GONDA]
Let me out!
What're we gonna do?!
Ah! Usui, help us!
She's crazy!
The president told him
to repent or something
and threw him in there!
The president did?
[IWAKURA]
Yeah.
(Boys laughing)
Looky! Looky! Looky!
You guys!
What the hell are you
doing dancing around
in your underwear?!
It's fun, right?
(Girls screaming)
GOOONNDAAAAA!
Stay in there and repent!
He's been in there
ever since!
Then he's gonna
have to repent.
Don't say that, Usui!
Please help us save him!
[USUI]
I'll pass.
So much for that.
We're screwed.
Now what?
Looks like our only option
is to steal the key from her!
That's impossible!
Not if we take her head‐on.
But if we use a surprise
attack, we have a chance!
If we used everyone,
do you think it would work?
Yeah.
[USUI]
Move.
Come with me.
So cool!
So strong and cool!
Make sure you fix
that door, too.
Woohoo!
Free at last!
[MISAKI]
The theme for...
this year's school festival...
is THIS!
New students and Seika High!
The school festival is our
best opportunity to improve
our school's image!
[YUKIMURA]
I don't know
about that poster...
[MISAKI]
That's why "New Students
and Seika High" is the
only logical choice!
Right now Seika High School
is perceived as rude, crude,
and socially unacceptable,
but with this theme
our image will be reborn!
By next spring we will get as
many female freshmen as possible
and cleanse this school
of its male stench!
But Miss President...
Our school doesn't
look like this at all.
Isn't it a little
too misleading?
(Slam)
(scared foley)
That's the whole point!
It's going to be up to YOU to
make this fantasy into reality!
The rebirth of this school's
image is going to depend on
us working together!
So did you finally manage to
come up with a proper proposal?
We'll sacrifice the...
Bellybutton Dance...
[MISAKI]
Some sacrifice!
So even though our last idea
was cool and amazing,
we might've gone
a little overboard.
So, we toned it down...
And we came up with THIS!
"Strip rock‐paper‐scissors
tournament."
Rejected!
But why?! This is a Seika
School Festival tradition!
There's no such tradition.
Yeah‐huh! We did it last year
and it was a big hit!
Maybe with the boys it was.
What's wrong with that?!
We're supposed to enjoy
the school festival, too!
The theme of this year's
festival is going to be...
"New Students and
Seika High School!"
So pick a freakin' idea that
will ATTRACT female students,
and NOT send them running!
So, you mean like,
a poolside bikini‐photoshoot?
Rejected.
How about a guy on girl
wrestling match?
Rejected.
A sumo tournament with
girls in skimpy loincloths?
Have you morons been
listening to single word
I've been saying?!
Get out and don't come back
til you have a REAL idea!
But you keep rejecting
all the good ones!
Why can't you just
pick one of them?
Because every single thing
you've suggested has been
totally worthless!
I think I might faint...
[SUDO]
Usui!
Huh?
[GONDA]
Usui! You've gotta
do something!
[BOYS]
Usui! Usui!
Usui! Usui! Usui!
Okay, what am I
supposed to say, then?
[IWAKURA]
Say, "Let us do the strip
rock‐paper‐scissors tournament!"
Let us do the strip
rock‐paper‐scissors tournament.
Uh?!
Usui...
No, no, Usui, you need to
say it with conviction!
Yeah but I don't really care
one way or the other.
[BOYS]
What?!
But they've got a point...
don't you think you should
take the guys' opinions
into consideration, too?
(Grunt)
[MISAKI THINKING]
I can't argue with him.
W‐welcome back, M‐Master.
Cat ears today?
[MISAKI THINKING]
I hate this guy!
Just because you have me
at a disadvantage
doesn't mean you'll
take me down without a fight!
[USUI]
Oh Misa, I'd like to
order please.
I told you not to
come here after school!
If anyone else
saw me like this,
my image as student council
president would go up in smoke!
Don't worry about it.
After all, THEY'RE hooked.
Huh?
Cat ears...
President Misaki, our precious
Misa of Maid Latte Cafe...
They're just like night
and day, aren't they?
[USUI]
Hard to believe they
used to be like THIS.
Now they're
your biggest fans.
I'm grateful to you
for keeping my secret,
but the school festival
is completely different.
The only reason
I haven't said anything
is because I don't want
anyone else getting in on
my secret enjoyment.
[SATSUKI]
Misa, would you mind
dropping this off?
Sorry for the wait, Masters!
Here's your Cutesy‐Cutesy
Rice Omelette.
What would you like me
to write for you today?
U‐um, then what about how
you feel right now, Misa?
Your wish is my command, Master.
Misa...
She's so cold‐hearted!
I know it's great!
I'm home.
[SUZUNA]
Welcome back.
What's this?
I won a prize from the
sweepstakes that I entered.
Wow! What is it, Suzuna?
What'd you win?
Rice.
Miso paste.
And soy sauce.
Uh... Suzuna...?
I know we're poor and all, but
you're a junior high student,
so why don't you try to aim a
little bit higher than that?
Don't worry it's not like I'm
doing this because we're
dirt poor, or anything.
I only send these off as
part of my club activities.
Oh, I see...
When you think about it, you're
the one who has it the worst
since you have to work
at that maid café.
You must hate it, huh?
Well, "hate" is kind of
a strong word...
So you DO like it?
Uh...
I guess when you put it that way
I can't say I like it either.
But the pay is so amazing that
it almost makes up for the fact
that I have to dress
like that...
Not to mention the fact that
my manager treats me well,
and that the customers...
They're all pretty nice, too.
So I guess...
I'm really lucky!
Boring.
Wait what?
Why did you ask
in the first place?!
Of course it's rejected!
How come?!
Did you really think
"Heart‐Throbbin' Cosplay
& Strip Rock‐Paper‐Scissors
Tournament" was gonna fly?!
Fools even asked the girls
for their opinions?!
What would you guys
like to do?
Uh... like a coffee shop?
Perfect. Class 2‐2 will be
doing a coffee shop.
That's not fair!
You're kidding me!
You tyrant!
This is exactly why
I told you morons
to come up with a proper idea!
(Whining)
Is it okay for you to just
choose for them like that?
It had to be done.
If we hadn't come up
with something Class 2‐2
wouldn't have been
able to participate.
We just want to make sure
that everyone has a good
time at the festival,
that's what's
important, y'know?
Don't worry. The festival
will be lots of fun, I promise.
Hey, do you think you can come
help me with this box, please?!
What the hell is
this supposed to be?
It's a planetarium where
couples can hold hands
and get lovey‐dovey in the dark‐
it's a really great idea, right?
NO WAY!
This is the opposite
of what we're going for!
We want to welcome girls,
not send them screaming!
[MISAKI]
Where are all the boys?
Oh, Misaki!
How 'bout you show me
what you've got... 'kay?
Sure! This is the
coffee shop's menu.
We tried to think of things
that would be easy for the
three of us to make.
[MISAKI] Mhmm...
Also, could you take a look
at our shop's layout, too?
Hmm... It would be better to
separate the guests from
the kitchen area.
Also, this menu has
too many items.
You should avoid using
any elaborate dishes.
The more requirements
there are on the kitchen,
the longer your
turnaround time will be.
And if you leave the finishing
touches to your waiter,
it will create more
interaction with the customer.
You'll kill two birds
with one stone.
Wow, Misaki, you sound like
some kinda expert?
Th‐that's because my younger
sister works at a coffee shop!
Ah‐choo.
Not yet, huh?
(Boys laughing)
Wahoo!
(Evil laughing)
Ooooo... AH!
I believe I said boys aren't
allowed to dress like monsters.
Huh? why the heck not?!
Because last year some idiot
latched onto one of the girls
and wouldn't let go of her.
We'd never do that!
Right?
(Girl screaming)
(Boy Laughing)
GOTCHA!
[BOY]
You're mine now!
[MISAKI]
Oh, really?
(Scared)
[MISAKI]
You got some kinda death wish?
Huh?
(Growl)
(Screaming)
You better run.
Misaki!
We look super scary, right?
Y‐yeah, super...
scary...
I hope I didn't
frighten you too much.
But I spent weeks studying
horror movies just to get
into character for this.
Are you sure it's okay to
blow‐off the boys of 2‐2?
They seemed pretty mad
when you said they
couldn't use their idea.
They'll get over it‐
I'm sure they're off having
another stupid meeting.
(Whispering)
This is perfect.
I know, right?
We should've done this
in the first place!
(Evil laughing)
I can't wait to see the look
on the president's face!
(Evil cackling)
Sakura's got a point‐
I can't imagine those dimwits
from 2‐2 giving up
without a fight.
Ooh!
Yes, yes! That's EXACTLY
what I've been looking for!
A cool but guarded,
intellectual maid,
a new character who will devote
herself to her master,
body, mind, and soul!
If this isn't the perfect
strategy I don't know what is!
"Character"?
"Strategy"?
Oh, Manager. You're getting
carried away again aren't you?
Quit trying to suck Misa into
your personal fantasy land!
Sorry. I couldn't follow
what you were saying at all.
That's fine‐ in fact,
it's better that you
don't know, Misa!
That slow but innocent nature
really suits your character!
We're so lucky to
have you at our shop!
[MISAKI]
I have no idea what
she's talking about...
Manager, I think that's enough
of that for one day. Okay?
It's not like Misa actually
cares about this job
or any of us anyway.
Honoka may look cute but she
has a bit of a dark side.
Don't let it
get to you, Misa.
I know that working at a place
like this isn't ideal for you,
but you're a hard worker
and a big help, too.
Personally, I love
everything about this job.
Making dreams come true,
making people happy,
and having a fun time together
is really wonderful,
don't you think?
And in order to make others
happy, WE have to be happy, too!
I guess that's why I get
so carried away!
Sorry if I get out of hand!
Man, they must think that
I really don't care about
this job at all.
[USUI]
Who does?
Ugh!
You're here again?!
What's with that reaction, Misa?
If you're looking to kill time,
go bother someone else.
Can't I get a little
of your time?
Ah!
Those are awfully
fancy panties.
That's sexual harrassment!
And they're DRAWERS
not panties!
There's no need to yell.
This is why I hate men!
You think you can just do
whatever you want to women,
regardless of whether
they hate it or not!
You're all the same!
How prejudiced. Haha!
Because of people like you!
Miss President if you treat all
men like they're your enemies,
then don't you think they'll
treat you like an enemy as well?
I don't care!
I hate them so being their
"enemy" is fine by me!
Well, okay then.
I'm just saying you
should be careful,
or you're gonna dig yourself
into a deep hole.
What's with him?
[MISAKI]
The school festival
is finally here.
This time next year,
whether our school's
transformation is
successful or not
will depend on how hard
you work today!
Yes, Ma'am!
So let's do our best, okay?
[YUKIMURA]
Welcome!
Welcome to the Seika High
School Festival!
[BOY]
So many girls!
Thanks very much!
(Happy giggle)
(Guitar tuning)
[IWAKURA]
Hey!
Everyone suited up
and ready to go?
Sir!
This is the day that we've all
worked so hard for!
We even had to sew
our own costumes by hand!
We're not gonna let
the president boss us
around any more.
If we pull this off,
we'll finally beat her
once and for all!
Ah! U‐Usui! It's you!
So which of these...
is mine?
You really mean it?!
Yeah!
Now we can't possibly lose!
Uh... This doesn't really fit...
It's not bad,
but it's not good either.
[USUI]
Why can't I just be
a samurai, too?
Is this it?
We have a winner.
The sword may be a fake,
but he looks like the real deal!
So I'll have to...
...wear one of
these too, right?
No way!
Hurry‐ someone find
something that suits him!
Go, men!
Thanks a lot!
Come back, okay!
Uh, what I meant was...
Please come again!
That's really what I meant.
Gotta be polite...
One takoyaki please.
Welcome, valued customer.
That looks delicious!
I know, right?
Looks like giving the guys
a strict lecture
on how to appeal to the girls
really ended up paying off.
I'm going to check on
the 2nd years.
Kay!
It's suspicious that the boys
of 2‐2 never complained,
but maybe they just gave up.
Ah!
Huh?
(Girls nervous)
[MISAKI]
What the HELL is this?!
M‐Misaki, it's terrible!
These guys barged in out
of nowhere and took over!
They said this is
their "territory" now!
What does that mean?!
[USUI]
It means...
This place is now an all‐male,
military cosplay coffee shop.
Obviously.
It sounded interesting,
so I joined in.
Get back, you!
Careful, or I'll
see up your skirt.
We bring you prisoners of war!
Your human rights
will be protected.
So just sit quietly and order
your drinks and you'll be f‐
Ah!
(Grunting)
All of you...
in the hallway‐ NOW.
Just what do you
think you're doing?!
What's the problem?
It's a cosplay coffee shop
like you wanted, right?
We even listened to
the girl's opinions!
We wanna enjoy
the school festival, too!
There are other ways
to enjoy it, aren't there?!
Why don't you make yourselves
useful instead of acting
like a bunch of idiots?!
Screw you.
You really think we're
gonna do what you say
when you order us around with
that kinda of bitchy attitude?
It doesn't matter what we say.
She never listens to us.
After all, Miss President
hates all the guys, right?
Let's go.
[WAITRESS]
I'm sorry, I'll go
get it right now!
[CUSTOMER]
Uh, this isn't
what I ordered...
Can I just go ahead
and leave now?
Please wait
just a little longer.
But they've got a point...
don't you think you should
take the guys' opinions
into consideration, too?
I'm just saying
you should be careful
or you're gonna dig
yourself into a deep hole.
[MISAKI]
He's right...
This... it's all my fault.
Wait a minute...
Please wait.
Huh?
Please help us with
the coffee shop.
I'm asking you!
[IWAKURA]
It's too late for that.
I'm sorry.
I'll help out.
I'll apologize properly later.
Right now, we have to get
this situation under control.
Here's your iced tea‐
enjoy, okay?
What can I get for you
today, young lady?
I'm sorry, if you could please
wait just a little longer...
Misaki... looks like
some kinda professional!
[MISAKI]
Alright, that's one coffee.
Would you like cream and
sugar with that?
[IWAKURA]
Huh? Usui?
[GONDA]
You're going in?
Our president needs help.
One cheese tart and
a lemon tea, right?
Will that be all for you?
I'd like to
order, please.
What can I get for
you today, Master?
Uh...
Huh?
Oh, crap!
I said it reflexively!
Excuse me, miss.
Might I offer you another
cup of coffee... young lady?
Usui...
I‐I'd like to
order too, please.
How about you, sir?
What would you like?
What're your spacing out for?
After all, you are a maid...
so please devote yourself
to your duties fully.
Right away, sir.
That looks like fun!
We wanna help, too!
Behold, Princesses!
This assortment of candy
and other crap!
Here's a refill on your
Iced Tea ration, ma'am.
May I take your orders,
m'lord and lady!
[IWAKURA]
Best coffee shop ever!
[GONDA]
This candy is the best!
[SUDO]
I know, right. I love how
everybody is so chill.
That looks kinda fun!
That's Class 2‐2, right?
(Excited chatter)
(Happy laughing)
In the end things worked out.
They did.
Why you...!
No! They ordered us to engage
in a battle of strength I swear!
[GIRL]
No we didn't!
P‐please don't hurt us!
[GIRL]
You're in trouble now!
(laughing foley)
(Misaki giggles)
Just don't get
too carried away, okay!
Did she just smile at us?!
I think she did...!
It was...
Really nice...
We know, right!
Hello, welcome to Seika!
Miss President!
What happened with class 2‐2?
Everything's fine.
Anyway, I'll take over
from here.
But...
You guys haven't gotten to
enjoy the festival yet, right?
Well? Hurry and up and go!
Yes ma'am!
It sure is exciting, huh?
This is our first time
visiting Seika...
Welcome...
to Seika High School!
Make sure to have plenty of fun
at the festival, okay?
Kay!
She was really pretty!
I think I like this school!
[SATSUKI]
Making people happy and
having a fun time together
is really wonderful,
don't you think?
And in order to make others
happy, WE have to be happy, too!
Huh? Miss President?
Not going to the after party?
You startled me!
I was just taking a break.
Welp.
Guess I'll join you.
Usui.
Thank you for helping me, Usui.
You were right.
As president, I should've
taken everyone's opinions
into consideration.
Looks like you've helped me
realize something obvious
again, haven't you.
So you don't mind
if I tell everyone
you're a maid?
S‐stupid!
That's completely different!
And don't you dare
tell anyone‐!
Of course not.
You're all mine.
My maid, that is.
[MISAKI]
Who do you think you are?!
[USUI]
I'm an admiral in the Navy.
I'm kind of a big deal.
Just shut up already!
Seeing Misa in an apron at
school was pretty great, huh?
Yeah and we got to
watch her all day long.
I hope they have another
school festival soon.
Maybe next time
I'll be a butler.
I'll just
ignore them.
[SHIROKAWA] We'll be the ones
[KUROSAKI]
...handling things this time!
I am the White God,
Naoya Shirokawa.
You can call me "Shiro."
I am the Black Lord,
Ryuunosuke Kurosaki,
also known as Kurotatsu!
And I am the Sarasara Lord,
Ikuto Sarashina, or Ikkun!
[MISAKI]
Hold on, you three idiots! You
still have to clean the toilets!
[SHIROKAWA] The president!
[KUROSAKI] Three idiots"?
You're calling us that again?
[SARASHINA] Misa!
Last time, you just went
"Eek!" and fled without
doing your chores!
Your punishment is cleaning
the toilets for a week!
[USUI]
Next time is
"Younger Sister's Day," huh?
Your sister seems like
the cute, comforting type.
[MISAKI]
Huh? Cute and comforting?
I think you're mistaken.
[BOYS]
Looking forward to it.