If you think you can get away
with calling our students
"insects," you're wrong!
I demand an apology!
Misaki Ayuzawa, would you
please do me the honor
of joining the
Miyabigaoka Student Council?
I will personally
ensure that you have
everything you need.
Please consider my offer.
Now you know what it means
to be the "dominant" one.
I don't ever want to
see you again.
Just leave me alone.
You're from...
Miyabigaoka, right?
Indeed. I am Maki,
Vice President of
the Student Council.
Can I help you?
Might I have a word
with you, Miss Ayuzawa?
Uh...
Gentlemen.
Sir!
Please accept these.
They are small tokens
of our appreciation.
No, please don't,
I couldn't possibly accept
such expensive gifts.
It is Mr. Igarashi's most
heartfelt wish that you transfer
to Miyabigaoka High School.
I'm not going to change my mind
because of a few gifts.
I'm sorry you came
all the way over here,
but please take these with you.
But these cakes were made
especially for you in my
family's very own shop.
What a shame to
see them go to waste.
Oh...
Please rest assured.
Mr. Igarashi has no intention of
"buying" you with these gifts.
Please accept them freely
and without reservation.
Uh...
Mr. Igarashi wishes
to work closely with you
in order to improve
Miyabigaoka High School.
That is his sole desire.
I'm home.
Oh. Welcome back, Suzuna.
Oh look.
Unfamiliar uniforms.
Are these more of the
Ayuzawa Cram School weirdos?
No, that's not it! Just go
to your room or something!
[SUZUNA]
I'll make go make some tea.
Please excuse her!
She's a little unusual...
If you do decide to
transfer to Miyabigaoka,
our president has said that
your sister would receive
automatic admission into
our school as well.
Uh, that's a nice offer,
but that's impossible.
The influence that the Igarashi
Conglomerate has over
Miyabigaoka is absolute.
For your sister's sake and
your own, please consider
our proposition carefully.
This shall only stand
for another three days.
We look forward to
your response.
But that's...
Mr. Igarashi shall
await you at Miyabigaoka,
to hear your final decision.
What's wrong, Misaki?
You're spacing out.
Uh...
Don't tell me!
Were you thinking about Tora?!
Who?
The Igarashi heir,
Miyabigaoka's Student Council
President, Tora Igarashi!
Misaki, you're not gonna leave
us for Miyabigaoka, are you?!
[MISAKI]
Of course I'm not.
You can't just abandon
me and Shizuko!
We rely on you way too much!
What would we do without you?!
Sakura! Please refrain from
such careless comments!
Misaki's future is of far
greater importance than our
transitory feelings!
Although we would
miss her dearly,
It would be selfish of us to
hold her back from going to
the school of her dreams and
realizing her true potential.
Misaki's future?
What if she transferred
and romance blossomed
be her and Tora?!
She could be Tora's wife!
Mrs. Igarashi!
She'd be living the
big life, courtesy of
the Igarashi Conglomerate!
[IWAKURA]
It'd be a lot better than if
she stayed here, right?
[KAMAKARI]
I mean, everyone
wants to go there.
It's an ultra‐elite private
school, we all know that.
No one turns something
like that down.
There's no reason
she should.
Well, on the bright side,
if she did leave,
we could go back to doing
whatever we wanted like before.
Ow!
Huh?
Why?!
I better not hear another word
like that outta your mouths!
That huuurt!
What'd you do that for?!
Even when we got in trouble
with those Miyabigaoka guys,
she believed in us,
and stood up for us!
Do you idiots even
understand how much
she cares about all of us?
Well, do you?!
Yeah, of course we do, man.
But if she says she wants to
transfer to Miyabigaoka...
Then it wouldn't be
right to stop her.
I was out for awhile,
but I'm back!
You turned into ash.
Now to take care of all this
backed up work...
Oh! Mr. Usui! Ah!
How many times do I
have to tell you?
Don't come into the Student
Council room unless you
need something.
Yukimura's terrified.
I DO need something.
What are you gonna do
about Miyabigaoka?
I am Seika High's
Student Council President!
If I left, the school
would go back to the
way it was before...
Still, it might be nice
to finally get away from
a stalker like you.
She's transferring to
Miyabigaoka?!
What's going on?
Did something happen
while I was gone?
Huh? Where's Mom?
The hospital called.
They needed her to come in
for another night shift.
She's pushing herself
way too hard.
She's a single mom trying
to raise two daughters
without any help.
There're going to be times
where she's going to
have to push herself.
Yes, I know, but...
Dinner is ready.
Whoa, What's with this feast?!
Did those Miyabigaoka
guys stop by again?!
No, they didn't.
I made all of this by myself.
Bean curd croquettes, bean curd
salad, bean curd imitation crab,
bean curd imitation
roast chicken, and
bean curd imitation sashimi.
That's ALL bean curd?
I don't believe it!
It is. Bean curd is cheap
but packed with nutrients.
Since we don't have a lot of
money, we have to be more
creative with our food.
I'm sorry for making things
hard on you too, Suzuna.
It's not your fault.
It's Dad's fault,
for running off on us.
Anyway, cooking
like this is fun.
Thanks for the meal.
Let's eat!
This is great.
Hey, Suzuna...
Would you like to go
to Miyabigaoka?
Why? Isn't that school
only for rich, smart kids?
It's not like I'd
be able to get in anyway.
But what if you could go?
Hmm... If we had
that kind of money...
I'd rather spend it on
REAL crab. Why do you ask?
Oh, I was just
curious, I guess.
It's hard to believe
this is all just bean curd.
And for dessert, we have
those expensive cakes
the Ayuzawa Cram School brought.
I already told you‐
they weren't the
Ayuzawa Cram School!
(Music playing)
Geeeez. Where did
Misaki run off to?
I doubt Misaki would want to
go to something like that
in the first place...
Huh?
Truthfully,
I don't want to either.
C'mon, I know if you
see them once,
you'll definitely
be hooked for sure!
Lookie, lookie!
Oh! Aren't they dreamy?!
They wear more makeup than I do.
"You times mishi?"
No, it's "Yumemishi!" Hehe.
You misread that
on purpose, didn't you!
No, I just really
didn't care.
I'm gonna go ahead
and call her!
Hello, Misaki?
[MISAKI]
Sakura?
Where are you?
Uh... I'm at Miyabigaoka.
Huh?
What are you doing there?
What's going on, Misaki?
Sakura... sorry, but I'll
have to call you back later.
Wait, Misaki‐
(Phone ringing)
Oh, Misaki?
The person you are trying
to trach is not available‐
What did she say?
It's no good.
I can't get through.
She's at Miyabigaoka
right now, isn't she?
Just what does she think
she's doing?
Why does she try to do
everything all by herself?
Don't worry.
I'll think of something.
It would be selfish of us to
hold her back from going to
the school of her dreams and
realizing her true potential.
She could be Tora's wife!
Mrs. Igarashi!
She'd be living the big life,
courtesy of the
Igarashi Conglomerate!
Don't worry. I'm sure
Misaki will be able to
handle things just fine.
You were right,
Sakura.
We DO rely on her too much.
So much, that we've forgotten
to ask her how she felt.
It's no wonder she couldn't
talk to us about
anything important.
So you're fine
with her leaving?
If she really transferred
to Miyabigaoka,
are you saying
you wouldn't be sad?
Sakura...
Huh?
If we want to get Misaki back,
then let's march
right over to Miyabigaoka
and bring her
back ourselves!
Yeah!
(Students chatter)
A pleasure to see you.
Is your mother doing well?
Yes. Where will you be
vacationing next?
[MISAKI]
I didn't really notice
the last time we were here,
but Miyabigaoka is like a
completely different world.
Sir, Misaki Ayuzawa of
Seika High School
has arrived.
Is that so?
Then I'll give her
a proper greeting.
This is a first!
That you've been so enamored
with a single girl?
I see, you think no woman
could ever be enough to
satisfy me, do you, Maki?
For the longest time, I thought
the same thing myself...
Hehe...
Miss Ayuzawa. I'm delighted that
you've decided to officially
honor us with your presence.
President Igarashi...
I'm see you've come to
discuss your acceptance
of my previous offer.
Actually...
Actually, about‐
Uh, whoa!
Uh?
[SHIROKAWA]
Why isn't Misa here
today of all days?!
Even though today is...
Shiroyan's birthday!
I wanted her to
congratulate me!
Ikkun, Kurotatsu...
I can't go on...
Shiroyan!
Pull yourself together!
(Crying)
Hey! Shiroyan!
Hey, man, c'mon...
[HONOKA]
Excuse us, Masters.
We may not be Misa, but...
...do you mind if we offer our
congratulations instead?
And we made you
something special!
We baked this original
Maid Latte birthday cake
just for you, Masters!
And not to worry!
This is free of charge for you,
our most loyal customers!
We're so happy.
But it has "Three Idiots"
written on it.
I feel confused...
If it's free,
who cares?!
Excuse me.
Huh?
Sorry, but Shizuko has
something she wants to say!
Is there no one here who will
go with us to Miyabigaoka
to retrieve Misaki?
Huh?
At this very moment,
our President is at
Miyabigaoka all by herself.
She is?!
If she truly does intend to
transfer to Miyabigaoka,
so be it.
But if we do nothing to stop
her, are we not truly at fault?
It may be selfish of me
to ask this, but I...
I don't want Misaki to leave,
I want her to stay here
at Seika with us!
All of you do too, don't you?!
You're right!
I can't imagine another
president besides Miss Ayuzawa!
Let's go get her!
Yeah, that's right.
Okay...
Let's go!
You can count us in, too.
Yeah.
Then let's go, everyone!
Yeah!
That's a rich school for you.
Having showers right next to
the student council room
is definitely not normal.
More importantly...
Why did this have to happen
to me in the first place!
It's gone! But I could've
sworn I put it right here.
Was it a different locker?
It's not here either.
There it is!
Gah! What is this?!
(Knock at door)
[IGARASHI]
Miss Ayuzawa!
Are you all right?
Um, I can't seem to find
my school uniform anywhere.
Oh, yes. I didn't want
the stain to set,
so I had one of our girls
take it to the cleaner for you.
It'll be ready soon.
That's great, but,
what am I supposed to
wear in the meantime?
What's that?
We already prepared
a replacement for you.
THIS is the replacement?!
What's the matter,
Miss Ayuzawa?
Uh, nothing, it's just‐
don't you think this is
a little too revealing?
What's that,
Miss Ayuzawa?
You accidentally burned
yourself in the shower?
HUH?!
And now, in an attempt
to conceal your injury,
you're being modest
to avoid discovery?
Uh, no, that's not
the problem.
Wait‐ now you're
saying you slipped and
sprained your ankle?
No, that's not it either‐
Okay‐ but you're
saying you've definitely
injured yourself
in some horrible fashion?
Are you even listening‐?
I'm coming in.
HUH?! Wait just a minute!
I‐I‐I'm okay!
I'm not injured at all!
Are you sure?
You seem rather flustered.
No, it's because the clothes
you gave me are embarassing!
You don't have to
lie about it.
It's not a lie!
Then show me.
Or I'm coming in.
O‐okay, I'll just put
these on real quick,
so just give me
a minute, okay?!
I'll give you
10 seconds.
Ten... Nine...
Eight... Seven...
Six... Five...
Four... Three...
He's counting down?!
What's his problem?!
Two... One...
And zero.
Give me my uniform right now!
(Laughing)
See?! I told you!
It looks weird!
And it's WAY
too revealing!
I think it suits you
pretty well‐
And you didn't have any
trouble getting it on, either!
I did it reflexively!
Anyway, I don't care
if it's dirty,
just hurry and
give my clothes back!
That would be a waste.
Besides, that outfit really
does look quite fetching.
In fact, it looks
rather natural on you.
Uh...
Maybe because...
it's what your used to?
(Gasp)
How did he...?!
A woman who'd wear somethin'
like this to work
is lookin' for the wrong
sorta attention.
And you've really
caught my eye.
(Gasp)
Forget about it.
My guys are holdin' things
down outside.
Let's get things started...
Get your ass over here.
So this is who
you REALLY are.
I'll admit it,
you had me fooled.
I figured as much.
You don't seem like the
sharpest tool in the shed.
This guy's a
freakin' jerk!
To be honest,
I'm really disappointed
you of all people fell for
my lil' act so easily.
I thought you had more substance
to ya. Guess I was wrong.
You're a babe,
a student council president,
and a maid
all rolled into one.
I'm excited to see how you're
gonna fit in at Miyabigaoka,
Miss President.
Wait a minute!
You've got this all wrong!
Guess I've got no choice.
This'll do, right?!
If it isn't enough for ya,
then you gotta do somethin'
more interesting.
"More interesting"?
Being the heir to the Igarashi
Conglomerate has its perks.
I can get whatever girl
I want, whenever I want.
Uh...
But I'm getting' sick of
them meek, obedient types.
I was hopin' for a bit more
outta YOU, though.
But in the end you were
just in it for the money, too.
You're just like
the rest of'em.
Meanin' as far as girls go,
you're completely worthless.
Hmph. You're one
pathetic excuse for a man.
Huh?
Have you always looked down
on people like this?
If you honestly believe
that everyone around you
is "worthless,"
then that's your
own fault, isn't it?
There's not a single
person in this world
who's worthless!
The reason I came here today
was to tell you one thing,
and one thing only:
I refuse your invitation
to Miyabigaoka!
I have no intention of giving up
my position as Seika's
Student Council President!
(Evil chuckle)
You really are...
an interestin' girl, aren't ya?
(Struggling)
Nice try.
You may do aikido,
but I do judo.
My groundwork is
my specialty.
Ah! No... Stop!
U... sui...!
Yeah. I think that's enough.
(Gasp)
What about my guys...?
They wouldn't let me in,
so I had to be a little mean.
(Groaning)
Sorry 'bout that!
Still, it looks like
you're the one who's
being really mean.
Right, you
perverted man‐child?
You've got some balls
talkin' to me like that.
Whatever.
Unfortunately, you're
going to have to find
someone else to harass.
You can't just touch her
whenever you want.
So keep your hands
to yourself.
Look who's talking!
Well, that's that.
Shall we go, Miss President?
Hey, wait!
Mr. Igarashi...
If you have anything to discuss,
I will speak with you
at your convenience...
as Student Council President
of Seika High.
Huh...
Usui! What are
you doing here?
I came to save a
certain someone from
a bad situation. Also...
You called for me
didn't you?
Wh‐what are you talking about?!
D‐don't be stupid‐
of course I didn't!
I have no intention of
giving up my position
as Seika's Student
Council President!
Even so...
good job back there.
(Gasp)
Here we go again.
Usui...
Uh... Thank you. Again.
Oh. I just happened
to pick these up...
Would you like a fancy
Miyabigaoka uniform
or the same old Seika High
one you're use to?
Well, which one?
Just gimme my old one!
Yet she took both anyway!
Huh?
Miss President!
Master!
What're you guys doing...?
Misaki...
Misaki!
I flat‐out refused
their offer to transfer.
I'm not going anywhere.
Ah, thank goodness!
Welcome back!
Master!
[THREE IDIOTS]
What's Usui doing here?!
(Misaki laughing)
She really is an
interesting woman, isn't she.
(Evil chuckle)
[USUI]
Miss President, I was the
only one whose name you
called in that scene.
[MISAKI]
Shut it, Usui!
You were just hearing things!
[USUI]
Well, I heard it
pretty clearly...
[MISAKI]
Where the heck were you anyway?
There's no way you could've
heard me talk that softly.
[USUI]
There, you see?
[MISAKI]
Huh? Sakura and Yukimura?
Why are you dressed like that?
[SAKURA]
I reckon we'll have some
mighty fine weather today.
[YUKIMURA]
Reckon I brought back
a big ol' peach!
[SAKURA]
Ah! I love peaches!
[MISAKI]
I am a native of these parts...
[SAKURA]
Reckon we'll be sittin' down
to eat us some peach!
[MISAKI]
Looks like I'll
have to bring
some friends to
slay these demons!