[MAKI]
In that case, we will now move
on to the second round of the
footman auditions.
(TORA chuckling)
[MAKI] There is but one
challenge in the second round:
[MAKI]
Please create an appealing table
presentation for afternoon tea.
[BUTLER A] Oh crap‐ I
don't know how to do that!
[MAKI] From the table setting to
the food and drinks,
[BUTLER B] Doesn't the little
fork go on the right?
[MAKI] all choices
are yours to make.
[MAKI] This will of course
require a basic knowledge
of table settings,
but for anything you are
unsure of, please use your
own individual tastes.
[TRIO] Huh?
[MAKI] The placement of a single
item can impact your display's
overall appeal.
[MAKI] Your attention to detail
will be key to your success.
Your time limit is 10 minutes.
[MISAKI, thinking]
No matter what they throw at me‐
I WILL save Maid Latte!
[MAKI] Now then, let the second
round begin!
[BUTLER C]
Which ones should we choose?!
[BUTLER D]
Argh, I got no idea!
[MISAKI]
Okay! Let's go, Usui! Gaahhhh!
[USUI]
Hold on a second.
(MISAKI choking)
[MISAKI]
Are you trying to kill
me or something?!
[USUI]
Who is gonna be having
the afternoon tea?
[MISAKI]
Huh?!
[USUI]
Who will this tea
presentation be for?
[MISAKI]
Aaahhh... Let's see‐
It's an elegant afternoon
tea at an English‐style
butler café, so...
[MISAKI]
upper‐class ladies and
married women!
[MISAKI]
Usui, look!
I got one of every cake!
Will this be enough or
should I get more?
[USUI]
Wow, that's a lot.
This looks more like a buffet
than afternoon tea.
[MISAKI]
I guess... it's not very
"elegant," huh?
[USUI]
Why not use something like this?
[MISAKI]
Oh, that'll do it!
[MAKI]
There are three minutes
remaining.
[MISAKI]
Huh?! W‐we have to hurry
up with the setting!
[USUI] Mind if I do it?
[MISAKI]
Uh? Sure... but somehow you
seem awfully confident.
[USUI] Scones should be placed
at the bottom of the cake stand.
[USUI] Go look for some
jam and clotted cream.
[MISAKI] Clotted?
[USUI] Finger sandwiches
should go on the middle tier.
[MISAKI] F‐Finger?!
[USUI] And at the top how about
we place some of those small
desserts you brought over. What
do you think?
[MISAKI]
Let's see‐ how about those
tarts right there?
[USUI]
For the tea, we should
definitely go with Earl Grey.
[MISAKI]
Why that one out of
all the others?
[USUI]
Well, because it's standard
for afternoon tea.
[MAKI]
Only 30 seconds remain.
[USUI]
Now for the finishing touch:
Some small flowers to create
a reserved
but elegant presentation.
Now we're done.
[JUDGE A]
Hmm... It's quite faithful to an
English‐style afternoon tea,
isn't it?
[JUDGE B]
The cutlery has also been
well polished.
Female customers would likely
appreciate the attention to
detail.
[JUDGE C]
What a splendid table!
[MISAKI]
(breath) Incredible! Everything
about it is perfect!
[USUI] Just who do you think I
am?
[MISAKI]
A mysterious, perverted alien
from Planet Pheromone.
[USUI]
Hmm... Yep, you got it.
[MISAKI]
No, but really, how do you‐
[MAKI]
We shall now take a short break.
Everyone, please take this
opportunity to enjoy your
respective afternoon teas.
[YUKIMURA]
Didja hear that, Kanou?
We get to eat cake!
[SHIROKAWA]
Kurotatsu, why'd you have to get
so hung up on the presentation?!
[KUROSAKI] Cause presentation's
the most important part!
[SHIROKAWA] Now we don't get to
enjoy the rich people food!
[MISAKI]
Say, Usui... Why did you
come to this audition?
[USUI]
Because being asked by a hot
Internet celebrity made my heart
go a‐flutter?
[MISAKI]
Looks like I'm gonna have to
force it out of you.
[USUI] Because wearing a mask
and a suit sounded like fun.
[MISAKI] Sadly, that probably
IS the truth.
[KUROSAKI] We're the ones who
want to sigh, you bastard, you
can't take that away from us!
[SHIROKAWA] You got to grab
[SHIROKAWA] [KUROSAKI]
Pssshhh...
[MISAKI]
Excuse me while I
dispose of this garbage.
[TORA, thinking]
Even makin' use of a loose
cannon like that, he gets
the job done perfectly.
[TORA, thinking]
That's Usui for ya, all right.
[YUKIMURA] Ah! There he is!
[YUKIMURA]
I thought that was you!
I didn't expect to see you here‐
what a surprise!
[USUI] Who. Are. You?
[YUKIMURA]
Eh? Mr. Usui...
That's you... right?
[USUI]
My name is Not Usui! I am study
abroad from exotic land of the
ice, the Iceland!
[YUKIMURA] Kanou, there's no
way that's Mr. Usui! He acts
nothing like him!
[USUI] Ha ha ha! You have make
[YUKIMURA]
But they look so much
alike it's crazy!
[KANOU]
Is that right...
[YUKIMURA]
That's incredible, right, Kanou?
I was super surprised!
[KANOU]
I think it's about time
for us to head back.
[KANOU] We still have
some cake left over.
[YUKIMURA] It would be a
waste to just leave it there!
[MISAKI]
I swear, those idiots
never learn...
[SARASHINA] Shiroyan!
Kurotatsu!
(MISAKI groaning)
[MISAKI] Ow!
[TORA] Hm? (chuckle)
(TORA laughing)
[USUI]
You sure were gone a long time.
[MISAKI]
Yeah. I was going to the
restroom when I saw HIM,
so I went into the men's room.
[USUI]
Why are you in such a bad mood?
Is it because I called you
"flat as a board" in front
of everyone?
[USUI]
Would you have preferred if I'd
said something like,
"Wow, look at these
rippling pecs"
[MISAKI] Who said anything
about that?!
[USUI]
Or did going into the men's
restroom make you so nervous you
couldn't "perform"?
[MISAKI]
(panic) Don't talk about
stuff like that, you stupid
pervert!
[MISAKI] (breath)
[MISAKI]
Eh. What the heck? Let go of me!
[BUTLERS] (noticing)
[YUKIMURA] (nervous)
[BUTLER A] What's that? A fight?
[MISAKI]
If anyone's in a
bad mood it's YOU.
Maybe. Do you know why that is?
[MISAKI]
I‐I think I do.
[USUI]
I see. Then... let's make up.
[USUI] If you act too reckless,
I'll have to punish you, Misaki.
[MISAKI] Huh!? (stammering)
[MISAKI]
This isn't some peep show! I get
it, Usui, so get away from me!
[USUI]
I'm so happy you get it,
MISTER Misaki.
[MISAKI] Oh, shut up!
I said I get it already,
[YUKIMURA] It seems like
they're still disagreeing about
[MISAKI] so hurry
up and get away!
[YUKIMURA] something, but at
least they're not fighting,
[MISAKI] And quit grinning
at me like that, you pervert!
[KANOU] Indeed.
[MAKI]
Attention contestants‐
we shall now
begin the third round of
the footman auditions.
[MISAKI]
Usui... I... I'll try my best
not to do anything too reckless
but I'm still going to... I'm
going to‐! I'm gonna give this
my all to the very end.
[ERIKA]
Aoi! Subaru! Over here!
[SATSUKI] That looked tough!
Are you all right?
[SUBARU] We're fine.
[SATSUKI]
Aoi! What were you thinking,
going off and doing something so
reckless like that‐!
[AOI] Yeah, yeah. Enough with
the lecturing already.
[SATSUKI] I swear! Ugghhhhh!
[AOI]
I couldn't just sit by and watch
as your shop got bought out by
some weirdos
who showed up outta
nowhere could I?
To top it off, they want to
turn it into a BUTLER café‐
[SATSUKI]
That's so sweet, Aoi.
[AOI]
That would just interfere with
my plans to remodel the shop and
make it cuter!
[SATSUKI]
Aoi, are you... plotting
to take over Maid Latte?
Anyway, SHE'S the one
who's being reckless.
[AOI]
What's that weird girl thinking?
[MISAKI, thinking]
Good... Looks like Aoi and
Subaru found the others
without a problem.
[MISAKI, thinking]
I know what I'm doing
is irresponsible...
[MISAKI, thinking]
But even so...
I can't turn back now.
[MISAKI]
This whole thing...
it's my fault.
[USUI]
Whoa. It really stayed in there.
[MISAKI]
We're not here to play around,
stupid Usui!
[MISAKI]
What is this thing? "49"?
[MAKI]
At this time all contestants
should have received a slip of
paper with a number on it.
[MAKI]
One member from each pair should
have drawn one card,
[MAKI]
which will be your order
for the next judging.
[MAKI]
The final round will simulate
customer interaction.
[MAKI]
For this challenge, the judges
shall act as your customers.
[MAKI]
Though you may be nervous, we
will be looking for grace and
refinement above all else.
[MAKI]
How well will you be able to
think on your feet and play the
part of a full‐fledged footman?
[MAKI]
This will be the most
important test of all.
[MAKI]
With that said, good luck
and do your best.
[MISAKI]
We lost one pair when both our
partners got cut, so I guess
this means we're last.
[YUKIMURA] Mr. Not Usui
[MISAKI] Gah! Get out of here,
Yukimura!
[YUKIMURA] This sure is scary
huh? We got number one so we're
first!
[MISAKI] If he sees my face up
[MISAKI] Unh...
[MISAKI] Usui...
(collapsing on floor)
[BUTLER H] Hey, are you okay?
[BUTLER B] Is he awake?
[BUTLER D] Hang in
there, you two!
[BUTLER K] Hey!
(MISAKI gasps)
[MISAKI] Oh?
[MISAKI]
Usui! Hey, Usui! Usui! Usui!
[MISAKI] (worried)
[USUI] Are you hurt?
[MISAKI] No, I... I'm fine.
[USUI]
If you're fine, then
I'm fine... Misaki.
[JUDGE A]
You there! Just stay put‐
we'll have someone look at you.
[USUI]
I'm all right, really.
[MISAKI]
There's no way!
Not after you protected me
from a fall like that!
[MISAKI] There's no way
you aren't injured!
[USUI] Argh...
[MISAKI] (shocked)
[USUI] Misaki...
[USUI]
Everyone from the shop is
looking on in concern.
[USUI]
If you're all right, then how
about you give them a wave?
[MISAKI]
But you... Your arm...
[MAKI]
Do you think you are
well enough to continue?
If there is any concern,
I can call a doctor.
That won't be necessary.
(TORA chuckles)
[YUKIMURA]
W‐Wel... W‐w‐welcome back,
M‐ister M‐Masher!
[MAKI]
Next up, pair Number 49.
[USUI]
Looks like it's
finally our turn.
[MISAKI, thinking]
The way he reacted...
His left arm must
really be hurting.
[MISAKI, thinking]
And then... there's
his right wrist, too...
[MISAKI, thinking]
Is it okay? Should I really let
him go through with this?
[MISAKI, thinking]
But... if I back down now...
(determined)
[MAKI]
The judging shall now begin.
For this round, I, Maki, shall
act both as customer and judge.
I look forward to it.
[MISAKI]
Thank you very much,
it's our pleasure.
[AOI]
It's started. Figures they get
that squinty‐eyed judge.
[SATSUKI]
This is going to be the last
challenge, isn't it?
I just don't want anything
else happen to them.
Please let those two
come out of this safely
[MISAKI] Welcome back, Master.
[MISAKI]
Please allow me to
take your bag for you.
[USUI] And your coat as well.
(Zoom!)
[MISAKI]
Allow to take that as well!
[USUI]
Allow me to show you to your
seat.
[MISAKI, thinking]
Good... I'll let Usui handle the
explanations
and I'll handle the
hard stuff myself.
[MISAKI, thinking]
Usui's arms are injured because
of me‐ I can't burden him
anymore than I already have!
[USUI]
Yes, Master‐ how
may we assist you?
[MAKI]
I think I'm ready
to enjoy my dinner...
[MISAKI]
Yes, sir! Right away! Zoom!
[MAKI] Also, you there.
[MISAKI] Huh?!
[MAKI]
If you would be so kind,
please bring me 10 or so of
those books over yonder.
[USUI] Underst‐
[MISAKI] Here you are, Master!
(heavy breathing)
[MAKI]
Forgive my intrusion, but I
couldn't help but notice...
[MAKI]
Are you attempting to
cover for your partner?
[MISAKI] Ulp!
[MAKI] Would there perhaps
be a reason for that?
[MAKI]
As in, you're trying to
avoid letting him carry
something heavy?
[MAKI]
My apologies.
I suppose I am merely being
a meddlesome customer.
[MAKI]
But if I am indeed correct...
then perhaps it would be best
if he was excused for the day?
[MISAKI, thinking] Oh, no!
[USUI] Master, you honor me
with your kindness. Thank you
for your concern.
[USUI]
But if we as butlers cannot
fulfill our Masters' orders,
then we serve no purpose, do we?
[USUI]
Please feel free to ask
anything of me.
[MISAKI, thinking]
All I've done... is make
things even harder on him!
[MAKI]
So then you're certain there
isn't some other reason? Would
you happen to be injured?
Not at all, my associate is
merely being diligent so that
I might perform a more important
task for you.
[MISAKI] Huh?
[MAKI] (confused)
[USUI]
With your permission,
Master, I shall now proceed.
[MAKI] Hmmm...
[MISAKI] Gahhhh!
[MAKI]
So this is the "task"
that you spoke of.
[MISAKI, thinking]
He can play the violin?
That's news to me!
But with his hand like that...
he can't possibly play!
[BUTLER E] Awesome!
[BUTLER F] I wish I could do
that...
[MAKI]
I see. Playing the violin is
a splendid "task" indeed.
I'm sure it will make my meal
that much more enjoyable.
[MAKI]
Please allow me to enjoy
this a little longer.
[MISAKI, thinking]
His face is looking more and
more pained.
[ERIKA]
Misa and Usui's round seems like
it's going on forever.
[SATSUKI] (nervous)
[MISAKI, thinking]
The whole reason I came
here was because
I wanted to protect the shop...
and the people in it...
[MISAKI, thinking]
I wanted to protect it,
no matter what the cost! But...
[MISAKI]
That's enough.
[MISAKI] Just stop it!
(music ends)
Oh, is something the matter?
[MISAKI]
My humblest apologies!
The truth is both of his arms
are seriously injured.
[MISAKI]
I believe he must receive
medical attention at once!
You there...
Is this indeed the truth?
[MISAKI]
You can see it, can't you?
He's obviously in pain‐
[MAKI] And yet... he said
nothing of it, did he?
(MISAKI gasps)
[MAKI]
Meaning that, regardless of his
injuries,
he is determined to fulfill
his duties no matter what, yes?
[MAKI]
He may be in pain, but for you
to take his work away
in front of his Master is
nothing short of disgraceful.
[MAKI] It would seem to me that
your relationship is lacking in
trust.
(MISAKI angry)
[MISAKI]
At your shop, "looking out
for one another"...
may mean sitting back and
watching as your comrades
push themselves until they
collapse...
But at our shop, we look out
for one another so that we DON'T
collapse.
[MISAKI]
It's because they support
me that I want to support
them, too!
[MISAKI]
The reason I've made it this far
is because, even though I cause
them trouble,
they've supported
me every step of the way.
[MISAKI]
Because this is
that kind of shop,
we can give our all to the
customers in order to put them
at ease and make them happy.
That's the kind of thoughtful
place it is, and I love it from
the bottom of my heart.
[MISAKI]
Now, if you'll please excuse us.
[SATSUKI]
Misa! Usui!
[MISAKI]
Someone! Please call
a taxi right away!
We have to get him
to a hospital quickly!
[ERIKA]
Okay! Hold on!
[AOI] They're all swollen!
[SATSUKI]
I'll wet down a handkerchief.
[MISAKI] Manager!
[MISAKI] I'm sorry.
[SATSUKI]
Misa, if Maid Latte changed or
moved to some faraway place...
[SATSUKI]
...what would you do?
[MISAKI]
Manager... If I thought you
needed me... I'd go anywhere!
I mean it.
[SATSUKI]
Thank you, Misa. You have no
idea how happy that makes me.
[TORA]
What gives? Why're you standin'
there in the dark like that?
[TORA]
And quit makin' that face‐
we're in public y'know.
[MAKI]
I built up an idea in my head
of how butlers and footmen
should behave...
and accepted no compromise
from my employees in regards
to my vision.
[MAKI]
I believed if we faithfully
recreated the English
class‐based society,
the customers would surely
be pleased, but...
[TORA]
You lost your way 'cuz
of what that girl said?
Hmph. You sure are a handful,
you know that? Well...
[TORA]
There's another location.
It's prime real estate.
[MAKI]
Huh? You don't mean the
Igarashi Conglomerate's...!
[TORA]
It's my land to do whatever
I want with. There'll be no
problem.
[TORA] 'Sides‐ lettin' their
shop go on the way it is will
probably be much more
interestin', don't you think?
[MAKI]
Thank you very much, sir!
[TORA]
I'll leave the rest up to you.
[TRIO] (in awe of AOI)
[AOI]
Hey, those three idiots are
being even creepier than usual.
[SATSUKI] (overjoyed)
[AOI] (shock) Yeesh, she's
making the same face!
[SUBARU]
It's to be expected, Aoi.
After all Maid Latte just
overcame its greatest
challenge yet.
[AOI] Yeah, but still...
[AOI]
Could you explain a bit?
Why'd those guys suddenly drop
their buyout deal for?
[SUBARU]
Didn't the manager tell you?
Mr. Maki decided it would be
better to build his shop in
another location‐ lucky us!
If he was just gonna build it
somewhere else then why'd he
even come after us in the first
place?! Huh?
[AOI]
Say, where's SHE at?
[SUBARU] "She"?
[SATSUKI] Misa, of course!
[AOI] You're finally talking
normally!
(SATSUKI giggling)
[SATSUKI]
Right now, I'm sure
Misa is with him.
[MISAKI] (freaked out)
What is this place?!
[USUI] It's my house.
[MISAKI] Yeah... I'm not sure
if I really believe you...
[USUI]
What's this? A visit?
[MISAKI]
S‐Something like that.
Where are your parents?
[USUI] Not here. I live alone.
[MISAKI] Th‐thanks
for letting me in.
(cat hissing)
[MISAKI]
You didn't... just
move here, right?
[USUI]
I've lived here since I started
school. You shouldn't have come
here alone.
[USUI]
Now I can do anything I
want to, huh?
[MISAKI]
(angry) I knew it! You have a
fever! It's true, you left the
hospital way too soon!
[USUI] Huh?
[MISAKI] Look, just go lay
down! I'm getting a towel and
some water.
[USUI]
I'm fine, really.
[MISAKI]
I said, go lay down!
[USUI]
Ayuzawa, really I'm‐
[MISAKI]
Don't make me say it
again, stupid Usui!
[MISAKI]
Please... let me take
care of you for once.
[MISAKI]
Shouldn't we try and get
a hold of your parents?
[USUI]
Don't worry about it.
[MISAKI]
Why'd you leave the
hospital so soon?
[USUI]
Being sick is boring.
[MISAKI]
Are you at least
eating properly?
(MISAKI sighing)
[USUI]
This rice has been boiled
so much that it's turned
into rice soup.
[USUI] President,
your cooking is‐
[MISAKI] I know, it's bad!
[MISAKI] Got a problem?!
Fine, don't eat it! I'll
eat it all myself!
[USUI] I'll eat it.
[USUI]
But it's hard to hold things in
my right hand, so you'll have to
feed me.
[USUI] Also, I'm sensitive to
hot foods, so you'll have to
blow on it.
(MISAKI blowing on food)
[USUI]
Isn't this touching...
I didn't know it was possible
to kill the flavor with your
cooking style.
[MISAKI]
Shut up! Just eat it!
Despite your complaining,
you ate the whole thing.
[USUI]
How could I leave any
behind? You cooked that
meal just for me.
[MISAKI]
Eh... Your clothes are all
sweaty, you should change.
[MISAKI]
Oh, it'll be hard to undo
the buttons with that hand,
so let me.
[MISAKI]
Hey... What are you looking at?!
[USUI]
You look like a scowling
delinquent.
[MISAKI]
Shut up! Just look out the
window or something!
[USUI] Yeah, yeah.
[MISAKI, thinking]
I owe this guy again...
He makes you think he's just
some trash‐talking, sexually
harassing, no‐good weirdo...
[MISAKI, thinking]
but when it counts, he always
comes to help me. But I haven't
done anything for him at all...
[MISAKI]
I'm sorry.
I feel like... I rely
on you for everything.
[MISAKI]
I came here to try and pay you
back for everything you've
done...
but I just screwed things up.
[MISAKI]
In the end, I can't do
anything for you at all.
I'm completely... useless.
[USUI]
You're a cruel girl... Ayuzawa.
[MISAKI]
(stammer) H‐How?!
[USUI]
You do realize that I
rely on you, too ...
[MISAKI] Liar!
[USUI] It's true.
[USUI]
You're just right
for me, Ayuzawa.
[MISAKI]
(embarrassed) "Just right"?
What the heck is that
supposed to mean? Quit
being stupid, Usui.
[MISAKI]
(swoon) What is this?
Dammit. You piss me off.
[USUI]
That's why I said you're
cruel, President.
[MISAKI] Why's that?!
[USUI] I can't be responsible
for what happens.
[MISAKI] What are you talking
about?!
[YUKIMURA]
Hey, Kanou, why are YOU the only
one who passed the audition?!
[KANOU] Who knows?
[YUKIMURA] I thought we were
supposed to be a team.
[KANOU] Who knows?
[YUKIMURA] Is that Mr. Usui over
there? Or is it Mr. "Not Usui"?
[USUI] What is it, Yukimura?
[YUKIMURA]
Oh! It IS Mr. Usui. Actually, I
have a favor to ask.
[MISAKI]
Yukimura, are you sure you want
to ask this pervert for a favor?
[YUKIMURA]
But I want to do something "big
brotherly" for my little sister.
[USUI]
Haha! I am Mr. Not Usui!
[YUKIMURA]
Huh? That was sudden.
Where'd Mr. Usui go? Huh?!
[MISAKI]
Just help him out, Usui.
[AOI]
Next time, Aoi the Internet
celebrity will film a music
video.
[USUI & YUKIMURA] Yaay! Aoi!
[MISAKI] So Yukimura and Aoi
are gonna get their own stories
huh?