Isn't last month's accounting
report done yet?
[MISAKI]
Also, are the locations of the
regular cleanings‐?
[SHINTANI]
Misaki!
[MISAKI]
What do you want, Shintani?
Let's go play!
[MISAKI]
This isn't kindergarten,
get out!
[SHINTANI]
Aw... Why does Takumi get to
stay in here?! (growl)
[USUI]
Skrak. Skrak pop. Crackle.
[MISAKI]
Good point, what do you think
you're doing in here?
[USUI]
Huh, but this the only place
I can relax.
[MISAKI]
If you want to read, go to the
library!
[MISAKI]
The Student Council Room
isn't a playground!
[KANOU]
I've seen that guy hanging
around Madame President
a lot recently.
You know anything about him?
Oh, you mean Shintani?
He's an old school friend
of hers.
Apparently, she looked after him
a lot when they were younger.
I could've sworn that when he
was glaring at Usui earlier,
there was definitely a giant
dog growling behind him the
whole time...
No way! You know pets aren't
allowed in here, Kanou! Aren't
you just imagining things?
No, that's not what I was
talking about, Yukimura...
Sure enough, our President's
been an incredible person since
childhood!
[BOY A]
Man, I'm hungry. Hinata, you got
any bread crusts left? I want
'em.
[BOY B] Bread crusts are a lot
better than you'd think, huh?
[BOY C] I want some, too!
[SHINTANI]
Oh! So you guys've finally
realized how good these are,
huh?
You there! How many times do
I have to tell you not to eat
those things in class?!
[SHINTANI] Misaki, d'you
want some, too?
[MISAKI] Of course not.
Hey, Hinata, did you talk to
the President about that thing?
Yeah, y'know, about that job.
Job?!
[SHINTANI]
Misaki, you're "Misa"?!
So THIS is where
you work?! HERE?!
[MISAKI]
Wh‐What do you mean?
[BOY A]
Huh? It's nothin' special, this
guy just went and got a job at a
gas station.
[MISAKI]
Oh, is that all it is?
[SHINTANI]
It's all right. I won't tell
anyone about YOUR job‐ your
secret's safe with me.
[BOY C]
What's this? A private
conversation?
[SHINTANI] Nothin' at
all! Well, I better run‐
I gotta get to work!
[BOY A] Goodbye!
[SAKURA] Well? How are things
going with you two?
[MISAKI] Gah!
Don't "Gah!" me. You have to
tell us all about Hinata!
In the chaos of our field trip
we didn't have the chance to
discuss things thoroughly.
Is it just me or does it look
like you two've gotten closer
since then?!
Could there have been some
sort of DEVELOPMENT?
There hasn't been
a "development"!
[MISAKI]
He's just an old
friend, that's all!
[SAKURA]
Ohhhh?
[MISAKI'S GHOST]
Tee hee hee, it's night time!
[SHINTANI]
I'm home!
Oh man, I'm starving! Huh?
[SHINTANI]
Whoops. I forgot to call 'im.
Hello, Grandpa? It's me‐!
[GRANDPA]
HEEEY!!!
Whatchoo been doin', Hinata?!
You ain't called or nothin'!
[SHINTANI]
You don't hafta get so angry...
Yer Grandma's been worried sick!
[SHINTANI] I'm fine! There's
nothin' to get worried about.
(GRANDPA taking heavy breath)
[SHINTANI] But sure enough,
I'm glad I came back here!
You find that Misaki girl
you was lookin' for?
[SHINTANI]
Sure did.
I found her right away.
At the same school,
in the same class as me!
Somethin' like that...
it's gotta be fate, right?
[MISAKI]
An anime cosplay event?
[SATSUKI]
That's right! The show creators
looked at everyone's photos
and gave us special permission
to hold this event!
Especially YOU, Misa‐ you'll
make the perfect Rose!
Magical Girls "MEI‐DO"?
[AOI]
Duh, It's a Sunday
morning cartoon.
Have you been living
under a rock?
I'M the only one cute
enough to play Mimoza!
[SATSUKI] That's
enough out of you!
[AOI] Hmph!
Anyway‐ here you go, Misa!
[SATSUKI]
I'll lend you these DVDs.
Make sure you watch them all
so you can get a
feel for the show!
[MISAKI]
All of these?!
[AOI]
They're on Season 4 this year.
There are almost 40 DVDs
on sale right now‐
that bag's not even half of'em.
[ERIKA]
But does she really
have to watch them all?
Just episode 1
should be enough...
[SUBARU]
And don't forget
episodes 12 and 13.
[AOI]
Things really start heating up
around this volume, so watch it!
[SATSUKI] (gasp) By
the way, Misa...
[MISAKI] Hmm?
Speaking of "heating up"‐
How have things been since
that "Hinata" guy figured
out you worked here?
What do you mean exactly?
[SATSUKI]
I'm talking about Usui‐ Isn't he
jealous?
Say, he hasn't come here today,
has he?
Now that I think about it,
neither has Usui...
[MISAKI]
What are we even talking
about this for?!
[MISAKI]
Usui's just a perverted weirdo!
[SHINTANI]
Thank you very much!
[BOY A] Shintani, you can go
home now!
[SHINTANI] Yessir!
[BOY A]
Shintani, lemme know what shifts
you wanta work for next month.
[SHINTANI]
Uh. Oh, sorry. I've got
tutoring next month, so... Huh?
[BOY B]
What?! You're not studying
properly?
[BOY C]
I'll teach you if you rub my
shoulders.
[SHINTANI] Hehe, I
can't trust you guys.
[BOY C] Yeah, right, you monkey!
[BOY B]
Want me to take you to your
apartment? I've got a spare
helmet!
[SHINTANI]
Nah, I've got somethin'
to do on my way back...
[SHINTANI]
That's weird...
It should...
be around here somewhere... Oh?
[SHINTANI]
OH! This persimmon looks
delicious! (Biting down)
[MINAKO]
Oh no, wait!
Come on, don't run away from me!
[SHINTANI]
Agh!
[MINAKO]
Oh my!
[MASTER]
O‐wee o‐wee. Summer
makes me want to dance!
Oh, no! The evil magic,
Mode‐De‐Trend, is forcing the
Master to dance terribly!
Let's go, Lilly!
Gotcha!
[ROSE]
Go‐ Mop Missile!
[THING]
(laughter) Blammo!
Wa‐hey! Wa‐hey!
[MISAKI]
Whoa...
[SUZUNA] Kids' shows these days
sure don't make a lot of sense,
do they?
[SUZUNA]
Oh, looks like Mom's home.
And... who's that...
[SUZUNA]
There's someone I don't
recognize. Could he be our
future step‐father?
[MISAKI]
Huh‐
Ah? Oh, hey there, Suzuna!
You sure have grown up,
haven'tcha?
You used to be so small, I
didn't even recognize you there!
[SUZUNA]
Here goes, Mr. Hamburger!
I been waitin' for ya,
Miss Cheese!
[SUZUNA]
Coming uuup: One Melty Cheese
Hamburger!
[SHINTANI]
(sizzling noises)
What the heck is that about?
[SUZUNA]
Oh, well... We're playing
"Welcome to Our Restaurant,"
it's a cartoon we used to watch.
[MISAKI]
I know that, but...
That's no good, Yoh.
You don't look like a
delicious burger at all.
You used to be much
rounder and juicier.
Huh? Well, what do you
think should I do, then?
At this rate, you're gonna
lose to Egg‐Burger Lad.
Right, Big Sis?
[SHINTANI] What should
I do, Misaki?!
[MISAKI] What are you
asking me for?
And what are you doing here?!
[MINAKO]
We just happened to bump into
each other as I was
walking home. He helped me pick
up some persimmons I dropped.
[SHINTANI]
Here, this too!
[MINAKO]
Oh, thank you so much.
[SHINTANI] Oh...
[MINAKO] Oh dear...
[MISAKI]
I feel like I've heard this
story somewhere before...
Thank you for the food!
[MINAKO]
You certainly have become
handsome young man haven't
you, Hinata!
[SHINTANI]
Have I gotten manlier too?!
You have, I almost
didn't recognize you!
Still, eating that persimmon
right off the ground was just
like how you used to be when you
were a little boy...
[SHINTANI]
I never thought that you were
the one who dropped it, Mrs.
Ayuzawa!
[MISAKI]
And what were you doing
wandering around my house
at night?
[SHINTANI]
Well, I was tryin' to look for
something...
Hey Yoh, do you still have a
huge crush on my big sister?
[SHINTANI] (embarrassed) Uh...
[MISAKI] Suzuna, where did that
come from?!
[SHINTANI]
Wh‐What do you mean, "still"?
[SUZUNA]
You haven't changed at all, Yoh,
you're as easy
to read as always.
[SHINTANI]
What's that supposed to mean?!
No way! I used to be way more
shy and stuff, so I thought I
hid it perfectly!
[MINAKO] That's right. You used
to stare at Misaki all the time.
[SHINTANI] Mrs. Ayuzawa,
you knew, too?!
So, Yoh, you were really walking
around looking for our house...
Being a stalker
is bad, you know.
That's not it at all... I was
looking for somethin'‐ that old
cherry tree.
I thought it might still be
around here somewhere...
Cherry tree? You mean,
the one you fell out of
when we were little?
Misaki, you mean
you remember that?
(YOUNG SHINTANI straining)
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Hey, that's dangerous!
(YOUNG SHINTANI screaming)
[YOUNG MISAKI] Yoh! Are you
okay, Yoh?
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
Yeah. I'm tough so I'm okay.
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Geez, what am I gonna do with
you, Yoh?
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Don't go running off climbing
trees anymore.
You have to promise to stay
by my side from now on, okay?
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
I'll stay by you forever and
ever no matter what. It'll be
you and me together forever...
Thanks, Yoh...
Wait a minute! That's not
how it happened at all!
[MISAKI]
You got hurt and had to go to
the clinic, didn't you?
[SHINTANI]
I was hoping you would've
forgotten about that part...
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
Nom nom nom... (chewing)
Okay, Misaki... I promise.
I'll stay by you... forever
and ever no matter what.
[MISAKI]
Also, when I said to "stay by
me" that's not exactly what I
meant.
[SUZUNA] Hot tea sure is
delicious.
[SHINTANI] Whether it's under a
cherry blossom tree or in a
I wonder if that tree... is
still out there, somewhere...
[TRIO]
Yay!
[KUROSAKI]
Sunday, how we've waited for
you!
[SHIROKAWA]
Today is none other than Maid
Latte day!
[SARASHINA]
And we've been especially
looking forward to today's
event!
[KUROSAKI]
I made sure to do plenty of
research in order to prepare
myself!
[SHIROKAWA]
Me, too! I got to watch a
morning girls' anime...!
[MISAKI]
Hello and welcome back...
[TRIO] Whoaaaa!
[MISAKI] Masters.
[MISAKI]
May you be lovey‐dovey through
Maid Latte magic!
[SUBARU]
Oh, no! Our masters have been
struck with the evil spell‐
Stress‐DE Shoulderitis‐ we have
to save them!
[ERIKA]
This calls for Misa... I mean,
Rose, to save the day!
[MISAKI]
Okay! Let's go, Lilly!
[HONOKA]
Gotcha!
[HONOKA & MISAKI]
Carlon! Papolon!
[HONOKA] [MISAKI]
Be healed!
[MISAKI]
Through the power of our magic
you've been cured!
[HONOKA]
Please feel free to rest here a
while!
They're perfect! Magical Girls
MEI‐DO! Their replication of the
characters is so flawless I
can't hold back my tears!
[SHIROKAWA]
I've only seen the show once,
but they're just like it!
[KUROSAKI]
They're the perfect fit for the
main characters‐ I feel like I'm
actually IN the show!
[SARASHINA]
But I never thought Misa would
go THIS far for us! (sobbing)
[SHIROKAWA]
Yeah, I kinda figured she'd just
completely ignore us again...
[KUROSAKI]
I think that's the best part of
the whole thing...
[AOI]
Messing up the names is totally
unforgivable!
[AOI]
Do you understand me,
Amalilith?!
[ERIKA]
Yeah, yeah, I've got it.
[AOI]
Today's event has to
be perfect‐ got it?
[AOI]
Say, Satsuki, lookie, lookie,
don't you think I'd make the
perfect Mimoza I sure do!
[SATSUKI]
No way! You're still in middle
school, AND you're a boy.
Right, Aoi?
There's no way I can put
you out on the floor.
Even though I look
this good?! Boo!
[MISAKI]
Another order: one Witch
Parfait, please.
[AOI]
Monama Sharte!
[MISAKI]
(foley) Stomachus Fullus!
What are you casting a diet
spell for?
I responded on accident...
I'm surprised you remembered
one of the less popular spells
that well.
Especially since you've never
watched the show before...
That's because I watched
all the DVDs I borrowed.
[AOI]
You watched them all?
[MISAKI]
It took a long time, but I
finished watching them late last
night.
[AOI, thinking]
She stayed up late to watch it?
[AOI]
Huh? He's just visiting today?
For a second, I thought he was a
regular customer...
[AOI]
What will you do? You gonna show
him your special act like
before? Hee hee hee! Ah?
[MISAKI]
Welcome back... Master.
Please... be lovey‐dovey with
Maid Latte magic!
[AOI]
Somehow... he seems kinda
different today...
[AOI]
Usually, he'd have a witty
retort or something sarcastic
to say...
[SATSUKI]
Maybe he's worried about Hinata
putting the moves on Misa...
[AOI]
I don't know what's going
on, but this is a job for
Mimoza to‐ Ah!
[SATSUKI]
I don't think so, Miss Mimoza.
[ERIKA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[SUBARU]
My apologies for the wait, My
Lady.
[SATSUKI]
How was it? Did you enjoy
today's special treat,
the Magical Miracle
MEI‐DO parfait?
[USUI]
It was fun. And very magical.
Good job.
[SATSUKI]
Is that what you really think,
Usui?
[SATSUKI]
The kitchen staff wanted
me to ask you for them.
They want to hear some honest
feedback about it from you.
[USUI]
When laying down the
quenelle, try using
something with a long tip
rather than a rounded spoon
to give it some shape.
[USUI]
If they practice a little more,
it'll be perfect in no time.
[SATSUKI]
K‐Ken... Wait... You mean like a
long spoon, right?
[USUI]
It could also use some gold
flakes on top,
or something fancy like that
just to make the presentation
more elegant.
[USUI]
And the sponge cake could stand
to be a little denser.
[SATSUKI]
Looks like there's a lot more to
this than I thought...
[USUI]
Would you like me
to write it down?
[SATSUKI]
Just who are you, Usui? I know
you're not exactly normal...
[SATSUKI]
But this is on a completely
different level!
[USUI]
I suppose I should take that as
a compliment, shouldn't I?
[SATSUKI]
Oh...?
[USUI]
No, it's just that
a certain someone
is always telling me
the same thing.
Just think of me as a perverted
weirdo if that's what you think
you need to do.
[SHINTANI]
(giggling) Misaki!
Let's have some fun!
[SARASHINA] Shintani!
[SHIROKAWA] What're you
doing here again?!
[KUROSAKI]
Wait, if you knew Misa was
working here all along?
[SHINTANI]
Oh! You guys came to visit
Misaki again, did ya?
[KUROSAKI] No!
[SARASHINA] It's not "Misaki,"
it's "Misa"!
[SHIROKAWA]
That's the law of Maid Latte!
[SHINTANI]
(chuckling) Huh? Oh,
You're here too, are you?
[USUI]
This isn't a buffet‐ are you
sure you're in the right place?
[SATSUKI & TRIO]
Oh!
[AOI]
So that guy's Hinata, huh?
[HONOKA]
Looks like things've gotten
pretty interesting.
This is what happens when people
act like total idiots.
[SATSUKI]
Come on, you two, don't make
such scary faces.
Oh I know! This calls for some
special friend‐making magic!
Ukin pawa‐kun, friendimus
become‐us!
[SATSUKI]
Huh?
[AOI]
Like that'd work!
Look like this situation calls
for Mimoza's boys'‐love magic!
[MISAKI]
Didn't the manager tell you to
stay off the floor?
(AOI pouting)
My apologies for the wait!
Here's the Magical Girls'
Russian Roulette Game!
[SHIROKAWA]
Whoa! I've been waiting for
this!
[SARASHINA] [KUROSAKI]
This is today's special menu!
[TRIO]
(excited cheers)
[MISAKI]
Alright, one of these glasses
contains the mystical wizard
potion.
The point of this game is to
guess who drank the magic
potion. So make sure not to give
anything away, okay?
[MISAKI]
If you win, you can get your
choice of a special coaster
or a commemorative photo‐
[TRIO]
The photo! Definitely the photo!
[MISAKI]
Yes‐ as you wish! Then I, Rose,
shall cast a magic spell on you
all!
Prepare yourselves for
magic Masters...
[SARASHINA]
Uh, wait! What kind
of spell is it?
[MISAKI]
A spell that prevents
you from lying!
[MISAKI]
Dream‐pa, droom‐pa,
no more lies!
[SHIROKAWA]
What's wrong, Kurotatsu?
[SARASHINA]
Hang in there, Kurotatsu!
[KUROSAKI]
I‐I think... this is
it for me, boys...
[MISAKI]
So, it was Master Kurotatsu who
drank the magic Wizard's potion!
[KUROSAKI]
Need... water!
[SHIROKAWA]
Kurotatsu!
[HONOKA]
See you again, Masters‐ come
back soon!
[SARASHINA] I guess we'll go
ahead and call it a day...
[KUROSAKI] W‐w‐water...!
[SHIROKAWA] [SARASHINA]
Kurotatsu! Whoa!
[KUROSAKI] W‐...Water!
[SHINTANI]
Oh? This looks like fun!
Do one for me, too!
[MISAKI]
Very well then, Master‐ what
sort of spell would you like me
to cast?
Uh well... How about some
magic to beat my rival?
If you need magic to win,
there's not really a point,
is there?
(sigh)
[SATSUKI]
That's exactly right, Usui!
There are some things that can
only be done without magic!
[SATSUKI]
Also, love spells are
a double‐edged sword;
even if they succeed,
there's no telling what
dire consequences they
can bring about‐
[HONOKA]
Oh no, Lilly! Don't say scary
things like that!
[HONOKA] If you use the wrong
kind of magic it could bring
scary spirits to your bedside at
night!
[HONOKA] Just thinking about it
makes me shiver!
[SATSUKI]
Honoka, I think we're talking
about two different things...
[USUI]
Thank you for the food.
Is something the matter?
Not really.
[MISAKI]
See you next time... Master.
[HONOKA] [SATSUKI]
See you next time, Master!
[SHINTANI]
Hey, Misa!
I thought of a spell I want you
to cast on me!
One to help me find what I'm
looking for?
What would that be?
You know ‐ that
cherry blossom tree!
[MISAKI]
Oh. Yeah...
[SHINTANI]
Hurry up and cast it!
[MISAKI]
Uh...
Okay, here it goes.
[MISAKI]
Droom‐pa, drom‐pa,
discoverus soon‐us!
[AOI]
Sulk...
[ERIKA]
Doesn't it seem like Aoi's in an
even worse mood than usual?
[SATSUKI]
He's just mad because I wouldn't
let him be Mimoza. Let him pout,
he'll get over it.
[AOI]
Even though my costume was
perfect and I helped, too!
[SATSUKI] Yeah, yeah.
[AOI] AND I gave you
all acting tips!
[SATSUKI] Yeah, yeah.
[AOI] I would've made
the cutest Mimoza ever!
[SATSUKI]
The only reason you bothered to
help out was because you wanted
to dress up.
[AOI]
It's not fair‐ I wanna be a
maid, too!
[SATSUKI]
That's enough already! Why are
you even hanging around here on
your days off?
Don't you have
anything else to do?!
Go out and make some friends
like a normal kid!
(AOI pouting)
[AOI]
What're you lecturing
me for, huh?!
[SATSUKI]
This isn't a place for you to
play around, Aoi.
[AOI]
Aah, shut up! Who cares if I
have friends or not?!
[AOI]
Besides I'm not the only one on
his own! That idiot Usui is
always alone, too!
[MISAKI] Ugh...
[SATSUKI] Aoi! Don't go
calling people idiots!
[AOI]
Hmph! That guy definitely
doesn't have any friends.
[SATSUKI]
That's not true at all,
is it, Misa?
[MISAKI]
Huh? Uh, you wanna know about
his friends? Does he have any?
Uh... Let's see... Maybe
Yukimura is his friend.
[MISAKI]
No, he's more like a pet. Kanou
is... a friend... Maybe.
[AOI] And what about you?
[MISAKI] Uh?
[AOI]
What are YOU to him?
[SATSUKI]
Oh my, Aoi, you can't just ask
outright like that!
[AOI]
A friend?
I don't... think so.
At least, I don't
get that feeling.
[AOI]
His rival?
[MISAKI]
Huh? That's what I thought
at first, but...
I'm not really
sure what he thinks.
[AOI]
You "thought"? As in past tense?
Then... here's a different
question: What is he to you
NOW? Hmmm?
[MISAKI, thinking]
What is he to me now...? How am
I supposed to answer that?
[MISAKI]
Uh? Wh‐What are you doing here?
[USUI]
Should I not be here?
[MISAKI]
Uh... No you shouldn't! It's
suspicious, hanging around back
at this time of night!
Someone might think you're a
pervert! What are you doing here
anyway, idiot?!
(USUI laughing)
[MISAKI]
What are you laughing for...?
Even Magical Girls take
out the trash, huh?
Don't you have some sort of
trash‐taking magic?
Why don't you try using one of
your magic spells from earlier?
[MISAKI] Uh.
[USUI]
Your face is all red,
Ayuzawa. Ooh.
[MISAKI]
Just shut up you weirdo!
It's pretty cold tonight, huh?
[MISAKI]
Aren't you cold
without a jacket?
[MISAKI]
If you're going to be out late,
at least wear something warm.
[USUI]
(laughing foley) Always watching
out for others, aren't you Misa?
[MISAKI]
I‐Is that bad?!
[USUI]
I'd planned on going
straight home,
but I wanted to see your
face one more time.
[MISAKI]
Don't you have any friends
you can go bother?
[USUI]
Do I look like I don't?
[MISAKI]
Hey, wait, did you hear us
talking earlier‐?
[USUI] Actually, something has
been bothering me...
[MISAKI] uh...
[USUI]
That question you got asked at
the end. I'd like to know the
answer.
[USUI]
Tell me what am I
to you... Ayuzawa?
[MISAKI]
Shut up!
[USUI] I see. So this is the
only way you know
how to express yourself
when confronted with your
true feelings.
[USUI]
Why don't you... just be honest
for once?
I said shut up! Everything you
say is so embarrassing I can't
stand it!
[USUI]
Aah, how cruel...
[MISAKI]
Look, just shut up already!
[USUI]
In that case... I'll express
myself through action, too.
[MISAKI]
What are you doing?! Let go!
Stop it, you perverted alien
freak! What if someone sees us?
Cut it out!
[USUI] Dream‐pa, droom‐pa.
(MISAKI gasps)
[USUI]
Now you can't lie...
Do you want me to let go?
You're not really a witch...
[MISAKI]
You can't use magic...
[SHINTANI]
Sure enough, Misaki is...
[SHINTANI, thinking]
No! That guy's got
nothing to do with it!
[SHINTANI] Oh?
[SHINTANI]
That's it...!
This is it! I found it!
I'm so glad. I can't
believe it's still here.
You sure have gotten big.
[SHINTANI]
I knew it... It's gotta be fate.
[SHIROKAWA]
Maid Latte's event was a super
big hit, huh?!
[KUROSAKI]
But that magic juice knocked
me clear outta the ring‐ talk
about a KO!
[SHIRASHINA]
That event sure got us Masters
right in the heart, didn't it?
Talk about a heart attack!
[MISAKI]
I have no idea what you Three
Idiots are talking about. But
whatever.
[SHINTANI]
Misaki!
[SAKURA]
Misaki‐Misaki!
[SHIZUKO] Misaki!
[USUI] Misa.
[MISAKI]
What's going on? Why are all
of you shouting my name?!
[SHINTANI]
We just wanna be around ya!
[SAKURA]
Yumemishi has another concert!
[SHIZUKO]
You don't learn, do you?
[USUI]
I just called your name.
[MISAKI]
What should I do?!