[MISAKI]
Eh...
One day...
Please, Misa!
[MISAKI]
Completely out of the blue...
Please become our Master!
[MISAKI]
I acquired some disciples.
Total: five.
Eh...
Whoa...
What's that all about?
The Pied Piper?
That stupid look on
all their faces‐
first years...
Aah, what an honor!
Our Master is actually allowing
us to walk her home from school!
It's a good thing all five
of us Inuyama brothers
enrolled at Seika High School!
And what's even better is
now we're part of the
Ayuzawa Cram School!
Our dreams of the ultimate
high school experience...
...are finally coming true!
Uh, do you think you
could you stop with
the "Ayuzawa Cram School" stuff?
It's getting embarrassing.
But Master! What other name
could we possibly go by?
"Ayuzawa Association" and
"Ayuzawa Club" just don't
have the same ring to them!
Besides, this was the
only name all five of us
could all agree on!
They're so loud...
Fine, just do whatever you want.
Thank you very much, Master!
I think you guys
have the wrong idea.
If you want a good teacher,
you should go find
someone else to bother.
How could you say
such a thing?
There's no need to be
modest, Master!
We've been very impressed
with your lifestyle!
My lifestyle?
[INUYAMA]
At the school festival
we caught our first
glimpse of your passion!
Your drive to whip this school
into shape is unmatched!
No one escapes your wrath,
even senior students!
Plus, you're at the
top of your class,
both academics and P. E.!
And you singlehandedly govern
the entire student body!
See! You're the perfect
master for us!
No, I'm really not...
well, I guess when you
put it that way, I am kinda‐
(Inuyamas yelling)
No! Master, you represent
our goal in life!
We want to become just like
you in every single way!
Master, you're our idol!
Yeah, President
you're our Number One!
Long Live
Misaki Ayuzawa!
Yaaay!
Well, this is my stop.
Huh? But we heard that you
walk to school, Master.
What are you taking
the train for?
Oh, that's right!
We've heard the rumors.
You have a part‐time
job, don't you?
How honorable!
Our Master works endless hours
to singlehandedly support
her entire family!
Ooh! That's our Master for you,
truly an inspiration
to us all...
In that case, we must learn
by her example.
Please let us
accompany you!
I knew this would happen!
I'm sure the job is just
as extraordinary as you.
Uh, no, actually
it's very ordinary.
You'd just be bored
the whole time.
Not at all!
Just being able to sit
and watch you work
would be a
learning experience!
We wanna come, too!
No, no, that's okay!
Just go home and, uh,
do your homework or
something, okay, got it?
You heard the lady‐
she said "no."
Yeah, so hurry up
and scram.
Got it, dude‐bros?
Uh yeah we got it.
Well then, Master,
see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Ma'am.
Yup.
I'm saved.
Well, see you at school.
We'll come with you
to the cafe!
After all, we have more
points to collect!
We hafta collect'em all‐
it's our duty, I'm tellin' ya!
Hey!
Then we're coming, too!
Yeah!
I already told you
"no," didn't I?!
Wait for us, Master!
Master!
I've gotta lose them somehow!
Ah!
Master! Master!
Did I interrupt
your game of tag?
Usui!
Master!
Where'd she run off to?
That's our Master!
Giving us the slip so easily!
(Sigh)
Saved again.
When did you suddenly get
so popular, Miss President?
No idea.
But it looks they want
to see me at my job.
Sure enough, she's super fast.
Sure enough!
Yes. Sure enough!
"Sure enough" you can't
let them find out, right?
By the way, I've
accumulated my points.
Huh? You got them already?
Is that good?
You stop by way too often!
But how else would I
get all my points?
Let's take a photo
together as my reward.
(Sigh)
Come on, Misa, you look
like you're in pain.
Just try and smile
like you normally do‐
act natural, okay?
Uh, sorry I just...
Master, we could take
one more picture
if you'd like.
Or would you prefer
to keep this one?
This one's perfect.
After all, Misa's at her
best when she's herself.
Aww!
Oh, Misa, aren't you
a lucky girl!
(Misaki crying)
It's a maid's greatest
honor to be so loved
by her Master!
Yay, yay!
Must be nice.
Is something the matter, Misa?
(Misaki crying)
(Students chatter)
Master! Good morning!
Uh... good morning.
Today we will do our best!
Mh...
(School bell)
Master!
Do you have anything new and
exciting to teach us today?!
Uh, sorry. I don't really have
anything interesting...
Well, it can't be helped.
Can't be helped.
Can't be.
Oh, man.
Huh? What're you doing?!
Job well done, Master!
Staaare!
Staaaare!
Staaaaare!
Staaaaaare!
Staaaaaaare!
STARE!
A simple meal of basic
ingredients‐ a winner's lunch!
Tomorrow, I'm going
to bring the exact
same thing!
(Sigh)
Aren't you going to eat?
Are you all right, Master?!
(Exhausted sigh)
President! There's an article
in the school newspaper...
Right. Let me take a look.
About the zone
allocation for
the cleaning project...
Yes. I'll make a
decision today.
Miss President, all these
were in the Complaints Box.
All right.
At tomorrow's meeting, I'll...
Staaare...
So that's the infamous
Ayuzawa Cram School.
Their dedication's
kinda scary.
That's enough!
If you've got that much
free time on your hands,
then use some of these
empty desks and study instead!
Yes, Ma'am!
They actually did
what she said...
Guess that's why they're
called the "Cram School"...
Wow, what a great
idea, Master!
Miss President, do you have
to work today, too?
Can we come with you‐?
Later!
Oh!
Be careful on your
way home, okay?
Wait, Master!
Why can't we come, too?!
No running
in the hallways!
Master, wait for us!
Ah!
Masteeeeeer!
They look like
a handful.
You again?!
Why don't you just tell
them to leave you alone?
Huh?
If you hate them, just tell
them to quit bothering you.
Actually, the truth is,
having them around
makes me kinda happy...
Ah! Master!
They may be a handful,
but they're dedicated.
I actually like them
quite a bit.
Hm.
Welcome to Maid Latte, Master.
Master!
There.
Would you like to try one of
today's specials, Master?
Or some tea or coffee?
[USUI]
And then.
Master! Wait for us!
Is today the day you'll finally
let us accompany you to work?!
(Heavy breathing)
That was a close one.
Y'know, your timing has
been way too good lately!
Why don't you just tell them?
Wouldn't they understand
if you just explained
the situation
to them properly?
Yeah, but even so...
I'm still a MAID.
It's not exactly
something to be proud of.
I mean, especially since
I'm their inspiration as
student council president.
They really look up to me!
I don't want to disappoint them.
So then you're just
going to keep running away
from them like this?
Running away?
Today's featured special
is pancakes with a
side of pure maple syrup.
Please relax and enjoy
your meal, mistress.
Master... what would you like me
to write on top for you?
C‐could you write "Love"?
Your wish is my command.
There. Please enjoy.
There's no way in hell I could
let those Ayuzawa Cram School
guys see me like this.
Please let me know if you
need anything else, okay?
Does Misa seem kinda
down to you or what?
Yeah, I wonder if
something happened?
[SATSUKI]
Oh, Misa...
Yeah?
These Masters would like to
challenge you to a game!
They're hoping to win
a photo with you, too!
All right, so you'd like
to go with a card game.
What would you like to play?
Speed, of course.
Don't go showin' off
too much now, Shiroyan.
A picture with Misa,
I can't wait!
Understood.
Let's begin...
You've got this
in the bag!
Remember how much
we've practiced!
Yeah.
Today is the day where
my blood, sweat, and tears
shall finally pay off!
Take her down!
Do your best, Shiroyan!
Here I go.
Kay!
One, two, three!
(Winner bell)
Huuuh?
So fast!
No way!
Is that even possible?!
(Giggles)
That's Misa for you‐
she shows no mercy!
That's why everyone calls her
the ultimate warrior.
She's completely
ruthless.
[MISAKI]
Of course.
If my picture got taken,
it could end up anywhere,
even at school.
Aah, dammit! I thought if
Usui could beat her then
there was no way we'd lose!
He's the first and only person
to have ever beaten her.
It was really incredible!
[SHIROKAWA]
The God of Maids
has abandoned us!
(Winner bell)
[MISAKI]
He beat me, but...
This is my first picture
with you, isn't it?
What did he do
with that picture?
Don't tell me he
took it to school!
So then you're just
going to keep running away
from them like this?
That's not it...
I'm not trying to run away.
I just don't want to
let them down...
If I think about it,
those guys used to
really hate me...
For the last time,
take those earrings out now!
Yeah, yeah.
I'll be sure to take
them out later.
Then they found out I was a
maid, and turned into THIS...
Collect those points
and try again, okay?
Okay! We won't give up!
Next time we'll get
even more points.
And then we'll get our special
photo with Misa for sure!
Yeah!
(Giggling)
Bunny ears! Bunny ears!
Oh, Misa!
I was thinking about making
tomorrow Bunny Ears Day!
I'm Bunny‐Bunny Honoka,
hop, hop, hop !
Bunny‐bunny, hop!
Maybe we should try
nibbling on some carrots.
Subaru, I don't think
you need those whiskers.
Oh, no! I guess they
make me look too much
like a mouse after all...
There! Misa‐Hoppity!
Misa what...?
Hop‐pi‐ty?
That's right!
Very nice, very nice!
C'mon, try saying it:
"Bunny‐Bunny Misa!"
So then, like this?
Bunny‐Bunny Misa...
Why're you holding
your hands like that?
You look like a zombie,
Misa Hoppity!
A hoppity bunny's hands
should be ROUNDED!
Try and look a little
cuter, GOT IT?
Honoka Hoppity,
you're getting scary again.
(Sigh)
If those guys saw me like this,
they'd never call me
"Master" again.
Misaki! What day is tomorrow?
Huh? Tomorrow? Hmm...
Is something going on?
If you don't know the answer,
it's all right.
As far as unimportant things go,
it's pretty unimportant.
Huh? What does that mean?
Tomorrow is Double‐Point Day
at the 3rd Street Drug Store.
DOUBLE points.
Can you believe it?
Yeah...
So if you need anything,
make sure to take this card
to 3rd Street store with you.
Uh... okay, sure.
Are you all right?
Uh, I might need some shampoo,
or detergent maybe...
No, I meant
"Are you all right?"
as in, you seem like
you're worrying about
something in particular.
Who, me?
No, I'm fine, really!
Huh...
Actually, it's not
just tomorrow:
there are special deals
for every day of the week.
So you're just
gonna drop it?
I've got them
all marked.
Woah, Suzuna!
Don't the people
at the store freak
when they see that?
Not at all.
They all help me
to get even more points,
which is a huge help.
Wow... Hm.
That's what's good
about you, Suzuna.
Huh?
[MISAKI]
I hope you always stay the same,
and do things your own way.
But, as for me...
[BOY]
Nah, I'm being serious.
Really?
I swear, man, really!
I wouldn't lie!
Hey, you down there.
You can't sit in the stairs,
you're blocking the way.
Ugh, it's the
friggin' President.
Let's go.
[INUYAMAS]
Master!
One, two...
Good morning, Master!
Good morning.
Master! Would you teach us some
of your aikido moves today?
Yeah, yeah, show us something!
Okay.
Ah!
This arm‐bar throw
is called "shihonage."
In aikido, you do not fight
by launching offensive attacks.
Your opponent
attacks irrationally,
so we don't match
force with force:
Instead turn your opponent's
force against him.
What an informative
demonstration!
Outstanding, Master!
Outstanding.
Aaah, so outstanding!
I just really...
I don't want them to be
disappointed in me...
This wind is crazy strong!
What's up?
Strange to see you
here, Miss President.
Usui!
Need me to jump in and save you
from those guys again?
No.
I just...
I came to clear
my head a bit...
I'm thinking about...
telling them that
I work as a maid.
When I think of them discovering
my secret by accident,
it just feels wrong...
I think that being up front and
telling them the truth about me
is the right thing to do.
I think it would be closer
to their idea of who they
think I really am.
So... you're doing it
for THEM then?
You're not doing it
to protect yourself?
Uh...
(Sigh)
That's right.
When it comes down to it,
I'm afraid.
Afraid of them seeing me
in my maid outfit,
and of their idea of me
being destroyed...
Afraid of being
looked down on...
Disappointing someone who
has shown you kindness is...
is hard.
Well, I wouldn't
be disappointed.
No matter
what you did.
Usui‐
And here's the proof!
Ah! What are you doing
carrying that thing around for?!
It's my good luck charm.
Good luck for what?!
Uh... good luck in love.
Ugh! You sonofa‐!
(Smack)
It's about time for us
to head back to class.
Sure is!
Oh well. It's your own fault
for trying to take it from me.
But... you...!
Oh no! Th‐this is BAD!
What should I do? If they
see that... picture...!
Should I go get it?
But even if you do...
Those guys down there
will get to it first!
What do you think
you're doing?!
I said, What do you
think you're doing?!
That's the
quickest way.
Yeah, to an
early grave, stupid!
If you tell me to go
get it, I'll go get it.
What are you talking about?!
Why would you even
do something like that
in the first place, Usui?!
Why, you ask?
Because...
I love you, Ayuzawa.
(Gasp)
Usuiiiiii!!
What is he doing?
What is he doing?!
I know, I rock.
Yeah, you do... you rock.
You big idiot.
Master!
Is everything all right?
Whoa! Mister Usui!
Hurry, a hospital‐!
It's not really
that big of a deal.
You can't just leap off
a building like that
and shrug it off!
Will someone tell us
what on Earth is going on?
Don't get it.
Just don't get it.
Yeah, what's going on?
There's something...
something I haven't told you.
Huh?
The truth is,
my part‐time job is‐!
[USUI]
Miss President.
You mean how every day
after school, I pay for
your services, right?
Wha‐?!
As my reward, let's keep it a
secret, okay, Miss President?
I...
I hate you so much!
[INUYAMA]
So Master is
Mister Usui's bodyguard?!
That's so cool!
That's our Master for you!
If she's busy protecting him,
then we'd just be
in the way, huh?
Who is Mister Usui exactly?
I wouldn't want anyone
else getting in on
my favorite pastime.
Huh?
I can't have "Misa" getting any
more fans than she already has.
Wanna take care of me
in your maid outfit?
Gah!
I'm leaving!
He's just a pervert!
A perverted alien freak!
[MISAKI]
I wonder if that fool Usui
is taking things easy
in the hospital...
[INUYAMAS]
Master!
Ah! You guys scared me!
Please, give your Ayuzawa
Cram School an order!
Huh?! Uh, homework!
How about writing a report on
everything that happened today?
And what about the writing?
Is five centimeters per
paragraph all right?
Uh, yeah, that's fine.
Okay then, goodbye!
See you tomorrow!
They really are nice guys...
Huh? Some trouble with the
students of Miyabigaoka?!
Well, that's bad!
A message from Usui:
"The next one is Girls
with Glasses Day."
Huh?!