[MISAKI]
How many times do I have to
tell you guys?!
Shirokawa! Your hair should be
black! And no earrings allowed!
Sarashina!
Shirts should be buttoned
and belts fastened at the waist!
(Boys annoyed)
[MISAKI]
Kurosaki! Wear the proper shoes!
THIS is how it should be done!
Hmph!
Eh?
Huh?
[MISAKI]
Don't come back
till you're decent!
(Boys horsing around)
I swear...
I feel like I'm surrounded by
nothing but lowlives
day in and day out.
Hey, Yukimura! Have you gotten
that proposal together?
[YUKIMURA]
Uh, Miss President, are you
sure this is really necssary?
A "Guidebook of
Student Conduct"?
[MISAKI]
(Groan)
You fool!
Of course it is!
Otherwise you idiotic males
would just end up slacking off!
[YUKIMURA]
Y‐yes, ma'am!
[MISAKI]
It's been several years since
Seika High School became co‐ed.
However, this former all‐boys'
school still retains an
80% male population.
I was elected the first female
student council president.
And since becoming president,
I've ruled al of these
buffoons with an iron fist!
This place has made my
skin crawl since day one!
Stinky! Dirty! Slovenly!
Powerless, the female students
could do nothing but
endure the male students'
blatant disregard
for common decency.
But something had to give,
so I worked hard...
harder than I've ever
worked before!
My dedication combined with
the power of basic manners,
helped me earn
the teachers' trust,
and successfully gain
the position of
student council president.
[SARASHINA]
C'mon, he's askin' you nicely!
Just take care of
the cleaning for us!
B‐but I can't...
I have things to do...
[KUROSAKI]
It's just one day!
[MISAKI]
Do your own cleaning!
[BOYS] Huh?!
If you've got
a problem with that
then maybe you'd prefer cleaning
the toilets for a week instead!
[GIRL]
President!
I'll take it from here.
Yes, ma'am!
What's your problem now,
Madame President?
That should be my line,
you three idiots!
What did you just say to me?!
Idiots who can't even
stay in dresscode
aren't worthy of being
called by name.
For the last time,
take those earrings out now!
This is my final warning!
Yeah, yeah. I'll be sure
to take them out later.
I said "NOW"
and I mean it!
Geez, shut up!
I SAID I'd do it LATER!
And I said NOW!
Ow!
Ah! She's a monster!
[MISAKI] These are mine!
[KUROSAKI]
She ripped'em right out!
(Running away crying)
Wait, damnit! Your cleaning!
[BOYS]
We will remember this!
(Girl crying)
Oh, now what?
[MISAKI]
Hey, what's going on here?
Nothing really.
I just turned down
her love confession.
You again, Takumi Usui?!
[THINKING]
This guy breaks hearts
left and right!
(Girl crying)
I've told you, you need to work
on your rejection technique!
Next time you make a girl cry
I'm coming for you!
(Grunt)
[USUI]
How many times
have I heard that one?
I wonder what's up
with the president
hating on the guy
students all the time?
Usui, you've gotta find a way
to make her cry "Uncle."
Do it yourself.
I couldn't care less.
Uncle!
[MISAKI]
Men who make women cry...
I hate them!
Huh?!
Both sides breaking at once?
Oh great! Not another
repair bill...!
I'm home!
(Crash)
Ah!
[SUZUNA]
Oh, Misaki.
You're home.
Suzuna! What's with this
death pit here?!
It's where I stepped earlier.
I think the wood is
rotten in that spot.
Yeah but did you really have to
cover it up with a newspaper
like some kind of hidden trap?
(Evil laugh)
Cunning, wasn't it?
There's nothing
"cunning" about it!
Suzuna, you didn't
hurt yourself, did you?
Suzuna?
I guess that means she's fine...
(Cough)
[MISAKI]
Hey, Mom!
Oh, Misaki.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You worked the late shift at
the hospital last night, right?
Your body's not that strong.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'll be fine.
I can't rely on you for
everything, Misaki.
I can take care of
myself just fine.
[SUZUNA]
We relied on Dad,
and he ran off and left us
with a mountain of debt.
There's no need to
bring that up!
Oh, your boss from Maid Latte
left a message for you
a while ago.
She said someone can't
make it so she'd like
you to come instead.
Huh? Really?!
Then I've gotta go
right now!
Why didn't you say so?!
Whoa, that was close!
I almost fell in again!
Misaki, do you think you
could mail this postcard
for me while you're out?
Another sweepstakes?
You got it.
Make sure you rest, Mom.
I'll be back!
(Crash)
Whoa! There's THIS, too?
(Crying)
Even though we're poor
we really need to find a way
to get her a cellphone.
(Doorbell)
Welcome back to
Maid Latte, Master!
Right this way, please!
Hey, Misa!
Yeah?
I apologize for calling you in
on such short notice.
No problem! It looks like
there'll be a lot of
expenses this month,
so it actually worked out.
Oh, Miss Misa!
Yessir?
Can I get one Cutesy‐Cutesy
Rice Omelette, please?
(Giggle)
One Cutesy‐Cutesy Rice Omelette
coming right up for you, Master!
(Groan)
I wish I could just quit
this place already!
But this is the only place
that works with my busy
school schedule,
not to mention they pay
more than anywhere else.
But if anyone from school saw me
like this I'd be finished...
Well then.
Ah!
THIS is surprise...
Miss President.
Takumi Usui?!
It's all over.
I'm doomed.
This is going to spread through
the school like wildfire.
There's no way I'll be able to
maintain my image
when people find out their
student council president
is a part‐time maid!
All the effort I put in
will be... will be...!
Time for a little break!
Ah!
Manager! Manager!
There's some unknown
lifeform in the breakroom!
Huh? What's going on in here?
Misa, are you all right?!
[SATSUKI] If you're not feeling
well you can just go on home.
[HONOKA] It was Misa
the whole time?
No, I'll be fine.
[MISAKI]
Good night, everyone.
Hm?
Oh, you're back to normal.
Wh‐what're you doing here?!
What do want?
Oh, nothing really. I just
wanted to find out for myself
that our student council
president really works
as a maid.
So, why are you doing this
kind of job anyway?
Uh!
[HONOKA]
Manager, I'll be going now!
[SATSUKI]
Good work today!
Ah!
Let's go somewhere else.
What the‐?
Just come on!
I see. So it's because
of things at home?
Are they that bad?
I guess.
So, that's why you got
a job at a maid café?
Couldn't you have gotten a
manual labor job or something?
I tried that already.
But I couldn't allow my
performance as student
council president to suffer.
In the end I couldn't
keep up with both.
Wow. Sounds pretty rough.
Oh. So even though you hate guys
you chose Seika high school,
because of the cheap tuition?
I guess.
[THINKING]
I have no idea what's going on
in this guy's head.
(Sigh)
[USUI]
My condolences.
I can't let this destroy the
carefully crafted respect that
I've built with my peers.
(Irritated)
Not something like this.
(Sigh)
Why can't I catch a break?
[MISAKI]
Three days passed...
[BOY]
So, for a maid‐
Uh, a maid?!
U‐uh, for a "maid souvenir"
my grandpa said he wants
a picture with a
high school girl...
Geez, he was just talking
about a stupid souvenir.
Oh yeah, by the way,
the other day, this made‐
"Maid"?!
U‐uh, that
MADE‐in‐Tochigi t‐shirt
I really liked
didn't fit me anymore.
Oh! "MADE"‐in‐Tochigi, huh?
Huh? What the‐?!
This is bad.
Every time I hear the word
"maid" I overreact like crazy.
Still, it's strange that no one
else knows about it yet.
(Evil little demon laugh)
Does he plan to use it
against me?
Or maybe he feels sorry for me?
He's annoying,
but that'd make things easier.
[SAKURA]
Misaki!
Sakura. Shizuko.
You tired
or something?
Sorry, I was just
thinking about something.
Misaki, you really have to
stop worrying so much
about everything.
We've got a really big
favor to ask!
Hm?
[MISAKI]
This is...
A sandbag.
From the boxing club?
[SHIZUKO]
It seems rather
intimidating...
It's blocking our path,
and we're unable to get to
the Flower Arranging Club.
[MISAKI]
I'll have a word with
the boxing club.
At any rate, it still
needs to be moved.
Stand back a little.
[SAKURA]
But it's really stinky
and really heavy.
Just leave it...to me!
We are the Boxing Club!
What's going on?
Put this up
before I take you out!
Yes ma'am!
Wow, Misaki!
You're incredible!
[MISAKI]
It was no big deal.
It was much lighter
than I thought it'd be.
Thank you! I love you!
Please accept this
token of thanks.
(Giggle)
Thanks you two.
Oh! Isn't that Usui over there?
Uh!
What are you looking at?!
Hmph.
[SAKURA]
"Hmph"? What's that
supposed to mean?
I have no idea.
But Usui sure is
handsome, isn't he?
Huh?
I heard that he practiced
Shorinji Kempo
all through junior high
so not only is he super manly
but he's super tough, too!
All the male students idolize
him and the female students
practically fall at his feet!
Plus, he's at the top of his
class in every subject!
And don't forget about
his looks!
He's a knight in
shining armor
in a school full of
brainless neanderthals!
But he's SO popular that
now he isn't interested
in girls at all. Boo!
Even so that doesn't
keep them from continuing
to confess to him, does it?
I had no idea
he was so popular.
I don't get what they
see in him.
[SHIZUKO]
Love truly defies reason.
I see!
Maybe he doesn't care
that I'm a maid
because he's just
not interested!
Uh...
What the hell did you
come back here for?!
[MISAKI]
What's going on?
What does he want?!
Woah, who's that?
He's hot!
Ah. Found you.
Is he making fun of me?
Is this some kind of test?
Or a challenge? Yeah, it's
a challenge, isn't it?
Fine, you son of a bitch!
Get ready!
Welcome back to
Maid Latte, Master!
(pfft)
[MISAKI]
I'm gonna kill him!
I'm sorry for the wait.
Staaaaaare...
Hey, hey Misaki is that guy
your boyfriend?
It's like he can't keep
his eyes off you!
No, he's not.
Wha‐?
This guy's backing me
into a psychological corner
and he's loving
every second of it!
(Evil laugh)
He had one cup of coffee
and sat there for a
friggin' hour, STARING at me.
(Sigh)
What an exausting experience.
I feel drained.
(Students chatter)
Huh? Usui, you're still here?
Yeah.
Hey Takezawa,
you and the president
went to the same
junior high, right?
Oh, yeah.
Has she always had that
intensity about her?
Nah, she was totally like
a different person.
I think it was around our second
year that she really changed.
Apparently she had
some kinda trouble at home.
She hasn't been
the same since.
Hold up, why are you suddenly
asking about a girl...
and the president at that?
[MISAKI]
He's here AGAIN.
Doesn't he realize how much
attention he's attracting?
[GON‐CHAN]That guy's here AGAIN!
[SAYU] Looks like he's
got his eye on Misa.
I just knew there was something
going on between you two!
I mean just look at
those puppy‐dog eyes!
Uh... his what now?
Wha‐?!
That's what his stupid face
normally looks like.
There's no "puppy‐dog" anything.
Hey, Misaki!
Good job! You got second place
in the school‐wide
practice exams.
Second?
Wait a sec...
then who came in first?
Mr. Takumi Usui.
No frickin' way!
Huh?
It seems she took
the news rather hard.
I'm working my butt off and
he's just laughing it up
and enjoying the show.
He's obviously
looking down on me.
Is that pornographic material
you've got over there?
N‐no it's just a magazine.
It's got some bikini pinups but
they're tasteful, we swear!
Confiscated!
That's not fair! Girls get
to do whatever they want,
but the guys get punished
for everything!
That's like some kinda
inequality of the sexes
or something!
Yeah if you're gonna be
tough on the guys
you have to be tough
on the girls, too!
You're right.
I will make sure to investigate
this matter immediately.
Innapropriate content is banned,
no matter who is
in possession of it.
In the meantime please let me
know what you would
like to read.
Both boys and girls.
Huh?
But that means you'll have to
look through all of it.
You're way too busy to do
all of that by yourself!
It's fine. After all it's
my duty as student council
president.
P‐President...?
Huh?
Uh...l‐last month's...
b‐balance sheet didn't quite
add up s‐so it's a little off...
and I thought maybe you
could take a look...
AH!
You messed up the budget AGAIN?!
Damnit, Sawa, you're useless!
[SAWA] I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Just forget it,
I'll do it myself.
(Coughing)
(Cough)
(Sigh)
I sure am busy...
(Cough)
What are you,
some kinda masochist?
(Gasp)
What are you doing here?!
You seem to really enjoy
punishing yourself.
Oh, but I guess
that'd be sadism.
Huh?!
You really oughtta give yourself
a break every once and awhile.
Seeing you like this is...
Oh, no...
That was a close one, huh?
(Gasp)
Get away!
I don't need any help...
especially not from YOU!
Yeah. Right.
(Cough)
I don't have time
to take a break!
(Sighing)
I have to go back and
fix the budget,
and then look through
all those magazines, too...
Plus I have to make sure I have
time to study on top of that.
I just think you have to
take a break sometime
so you don't get burnt out.
I don't need any help...
especially not from YOU!
I'm never one to half‐ass
any of my duties...
I feel like crap.
No way!
Is that the president?
Oh, it is.
Seriously? A MAID?
Oh, this is rich!
We gotta call everyone up!
Y'know, my ears really hurt.
I gotta get a pic!
[MISAKI]
This is the worst.
Tryin' to run away?
I don't think so,
Miss President.
You harass guys left
and right at school,
but you're
actually a maid?
Let go!
Oh no you're gonna stay
and serve us personally.
Alright, say cheese!
Say "Master"
or something.
[KUROSAKI]
Yeah, that's what you're
supposed to say, right?
[MISAKI]
I don't... have any strength...
So even the president can
look girly when she wants.
Dressing like this
makes you even cuter‐
That doesn't give you
permission to touch her.
Oh man, you're burning up.
[BOYS] Usui!
(Cough)
Ah!
Uh... I'm sorry...
(Labored beathing)
I'm sorry, Usui.
It's all right.
Just get some rest.
[MINAKO]
Misaki?
I was so worried.
Your boss called and
told me you'd collapsed.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Just go on back to bed
and relax.
[MISAKI]
If I can rest for just a day,
I'm sure my head will
clear right up.
[USUI]
Don't worry, those guys
aren't going to out you.
Really?
I find that hard to believe.
Did you do something to them?
Not really.
I just told them I was
enjoying our little secret...
And that I'd appreciate it
if they didn't say anything.
So you have been
enjoying yourself.
If I told you I was worried
you'd just get mad, right?
Well, it's not like
it'd be a big deal
if the school
found out anyway.
After all, it's not like
being a maid is against
the law or anything.
And wearing a maid outfit
doesn't change the fact
that you're strong,
or smart, or
incredibly hardworking.
I think you should be proud.
You know, yesterday...
I couldn't stop thinking
about what an infuriating
person you are.
But what I said now
was pretty good, right?
I feel like I'm in a race
running as fast and
hard as I can,
but no matter how far I go
you're always right there
in front of me,
running with
no trouble at all.
Sometimes you even run backwards
and call out to me,
like you're taunting me.
[USUI] You okay? Come on!
I hate losing, so that
really pisses me off.
But this time, the fact that
you were running ahead
really saved me.
But watch out!
Because I'm catching up to you,
and soon enough I will
leave you in the dust.
Then I'm gonna be the one
running ahead
and worrying about you,
Usui Takumi, mark my words.
Oh that's right.
Thanks for the scarf,
and for everything else, too.
I don't want to feel
like I owe you,
so I wanted to thank you somehow
but I couldn't come up
with anything.
So just tell me what you want.
Well...
Uh! Whatever you want.
For just one day, I want you
to be my personal maid.
Ah!
[MISAKI]
Usui! What are you thinking,
you idiot?!
[USUI]
Where's the harm? Stingy.
Shut up, pervert!
Wait, I thought you
didn't like girls!
Aah, such fun.
I shouldn't have made
friends with this fool.
As president, I'm
super busy preparing for
the school festival.
Huh? President?
I have to get more
girl students, or else
I'll fail as president!
What's with
all the cat ears?
First, there's the
theme of the festival.
How about, the "Men of
Seika High School"!
Yes, it's decided!
I'll show you I can
change this school!
Very well,
Miss President.