(SUZUNA eating)
Oh, that's right, I almost
forgot‐ I also won a trip
overseas.
But getting a passport is a
pain, and I still have to come
up with the money for the hotel
and stuff,
so I'll just give it to
someone else in the club.
Maybe I should try rice... with
watermelon cooked into it.
No, I'd better not.
[MISAKI]
Manager's younger sister has a
beach house that we're visiting
for our summer vacation.
Our first day was long and
stressful, and now we're facing
the morning of the second.
Still, everyone was up late
enjoying themselves last night,
so instead of "morning," it's
more like "before noon."
[USUI]
Ah...
Good morning to you, Miss Misa.
(embarrassed)
[MISAKI, mumbled]
G‐good morning... Usui.
(USUI yawns)
[MISAKI, thinking]
Is he not a morning person?
(big roar)
[USUI]
What are you doing, Misa?
Just waking myself up!
Don't mind me! (breaths)
That's seems less like
a way of waking up
and more like a way of putting
yourself to sleep forever.
What would give you that
idea, Usui? See, look at
how awake I am.
[NAGISA]
I've taken you in, so try to put
yourself in my shoes!
Why do you always have
to dress like that?
What's the big deal?!
Dressing this way is
natural for me!
Yeah, yeah. I've heard
it all from you before.
Hmph.
(sigh)
Fine‐ I'll let you wear
whatever you want, okay.
Huh? You really mean it?!
If you win today's beach
volleyball tournament,
that is. See!
(MISAKI and USUI intrigued)
I can really wear whatever I
want? You won't complain or nag
anymore? Or take my wig away?
That's right. If you'd
prefer, I'll even consider
letting you go home.
You want to get away from
all this sun, right?
Mhmmm!
I can make that happen for ya.
If you can win this tournament
like a man, my brother,
your father will probably
accept you a little more.
Auntie Nagisa!
Thank you, Aunt Nagisa! Let's do
our best, okay? I'm gonna win!
Huh? What are you
talking about, Aoi?
The tournament. Each pair
has to be boy‐girl, right?
Yes, that's right.
Aunt Nagisa, you'll be my
partner, won't you?
After all, you were
last year's champion!
Wow, so Nagisa won the
tournament last year?
[AOI]
That's not fair!
This year the tournament
has an age limit,
so too bad for you
I can't compete!
If you want to enter you'll have
to find somebody else to be your
partner!
(AOI scared)
Th‐that's impossible! Come on!
I don't even have any friends
here, I'll never find anyone!
"Impossible"?
So you're gonna give up
just like that, huh, Aoi?
(AOI irritated)
[NAGISA]
Well, fine by me. Guess I'll
just have you work here for the
rest of summer as a MAN.
[AOI]
I won't give up!
I won't give up that easily.
Not after everything that I've
gone through.
I don't care if people think
I'm weird or gross, or if they
laugh... because this is who I
am!
And I'm not going to change
myself for anyone!
I'm going to find a partner.
[NAGISA]
Heh. No matter what he says,
he's a boy at heart.
Poor Aoi...
[AOI, thinking]
Finding a girl who can play
beach volleyball well isn't
going to be easy...
Uh...
(MISAKI humming)
Oh, hey Aoi, perfect timing!
I was just thinking that
while I was here it'd be
nice to play some volleyball.
Do you know where I could get
in on some volleyball action?
Uh?
Misa, you're going to enter the
beach volleyball competition?
I want you to win and become
the Beach Princess! Make sure
to kick their butts, okay?
(MISAKI slurping)
What's the Beach Princess?
[SATSUKI] You don't know?
[MISAKI] Uh, no...
[SATSUKI]
The boy‐girl pair that wins will
be crowned this year's prince
and princess at the festival!
A big celebration is held for
the winners, and they even have
a commemorative photoshoot!
Plus they give you bunch of cute
bikinis for you to take pictures
in!
[MISAKI]
Oh, yeah? I'm not really
interested in that...
But my motto is, "Win no matter
what." And we're definitely
gonna win! (slurping)
Well, Aoi and I have
some practicing to do.
[ALL]
You and Aoi are on
a team together?
[USUI]
Misa...
Hm? Oh, it's you, Usui.
[USUI] Have you ever
played beach volleyball?
[MISAKI] Nope.
It's not like indoor volleyball.
It's completely different.
That's true. It's a lot
harder to run in the sand,
but we should be fine.
You seem to be pretty
confident about that.
Do I?
No, I think I'm more
determined than anything.
I'm not confident at all.
Yeah. I'm simply
determined that I WILL win.
In Aoi's eyes... there was this
look of serious determination...
when I saw that I knew I had to
do my best to help him.
Still, since I don't have any
experience, I don't know how
helpful I'll actually be.
In that case, why doesn't he
get someone else to help him?
Huh?
Don't do it, Ayuzawa.
Wh‐What are you talking about?
I don't understand you at all!
I have to go now.
Huh?
[MISAKI]
I'm sorry!
[AOI]
You're late!
[MAN]
Excuse me...
Oh, yes! Welcome!
[ANNOUNCER]
It's here again, folks,
the event you've all been
waiting for!
The Viva Royale Beach
Volleyball Tournament!
But the players will be up
against more than each other!
They'll have to take on the
scorching hot sun, the
hard‐to‐move‐in sand,
and the wildly blowing wind
if they want to win!
Who will be the ones to use
teamwork to win the tournament
and be crowned prince and
princess at tonight's festival?
Okay everyone, let's get
this party started!
(CROWD cheering)
[SATSUKI] It's just about time.
[HONOKA] But where are Misa and
Aoi?
They've been gone this
whole time practicing...
[BOTH]
We will win, no matter WHAT!
(CROWD freaking out)
Is that Misa and Aoi over
there? They look like hell,
huh? And then some.
[SATSUKI]
What's happened to them in
such a short amount of time?
Just what kind of
training did they do...?
(uneasy)
Dammit! That wasn't enough
practice time at all!
Don't worry‐ we've got this!
We'll definitely win. I've
seen just how serious you are!
Let's go, Misakichi!
"Misakichi"?
[ERIKA]
Oh, there you
are. What's up?
You guys look like you're
ready to go all out.
Huh? Erika?
Uh! And Usui, too?!
What are you two doing here?
When I heard you were
entering the tournament,
I felt like joining
in the fun!
So I asked Usui here,
and he agreed to be my teammate!
Beach volleyball sure is
a lot of fun, isn't it?
I just love it!
"Okay"? Usui, do you even care
about this?
What are you competing for,
it's not like you're really
interested, right?
Victory will be MINE.
GAHHHHH!
[MISAKI]
FINE! THEN BRING IT ON!
(MISAKI & AOI chanting "Gonna
win, gonna win" over and over)
[MISAKI]
Eat this!
[BOY] Ahhh!
[ANNOUNCER]
The Ayuzawa‐Hyoudou pair wins!
[BOTH]
Yeah!
(MISAKI & AOI chanting "Gonna
win, gonna win" over and over)
[MISAKI]
Read the direction of the wind!
[AOI]
Conquer the sand!
Eat thiiis!
[MISAKI]
Hyaaa!
(BOTH scared)
[ANNOUNCER] The Ayuzawa‐Hyoudou
pair wins!
[BOTH] Ah‐ha!
(MISAKI & AOI chanting "Gonna
win, gonna win" over and over)
[MISAKI]
Come at us with everything
you got! BRING IT ONNNN!
(BOY & GIRL scared)
[MISAKI]
Eat this!
[BOTH]
EEEEEK!
(MISAKI & AOI powering up)
[ANNOUNCER]
The Ayuzawa‐Hyoudou pair
moves to the playoffs!
(growling) HA!
[HONOKA]
Those two are so strong...
it's actually kinda scary.
[SUBARU]
With every match they win, they
make the other teams lose their
will to fight even more.
[Aoi] No mercy!
[Misaki] Destroy the
competition!
[Nagisa] They're great.
[GIRLS]
(squealing) He's so cool!
I was hoping it'd
turn out like this.
If we win this, I'm FREE!
(laughing) Looks like we better
get serious about this, then...
[AOI]
Go! Final battle!
Get ready, Usui! I won't
be going easy on you!
[MISAKI, thinking]
What's with him? What did he
even enter this tournament
for in the first place?!
He knows how important this
is to Aoi, so why's he
playing against us?
[BOY A]
Which one of those girls
do you think'll be this
year's princess?
[BOY B]
Dunno but I hope it's the
sexier one, she's a real babe.
[BOY A]
Nah, that guy she's playing with
is obviously her boyfriend.
That other chick is who you
should have your eye on!
[BOY B]
Is her partner her younger
brother? They don't look like
they're together.
[MISAKI, thinking]
Maybe... Usui defeated
the other, strong teams
so Aoi could get to the
finals without any problems.
Could that be it...?
Yeah, maybe he's
trying to help us...
[MISAKI, thinking]
Because when it counts,
he always does...
[ANNOUNCER]
Let the final game start!
Dah!
Dohhh
(determined)
Hwah!
(grunting)
Dah!
There!
(gasping)
[ANNOUNCER]
The Usui‐Erika pair
take the first set!
(heavy breathing)
[AOI] They're good.
Looks like I underestimated
him... that damn Usui is
serious...
[ERIKA] Yay! High five!
[MISAKI] After all that, he
didn't even break a sweat!
[USUI] Yeah!
(concerned)
That guy really knows what
he's doing. Looks like he'll
be a tough opponent to beat.
[ANNOUNCER]
The second set will now begin!
(panting)
Dammit‐ what kind
of monster is he?
[MISAKI]
He's not even out of
breath... but he's STILL
kicking our butts!
[AOI]
Cuz he's aiming the ball to
where we can barely reach it.
But this isn't over yet,
I won't be defeated!
Let's do this, Aoi.
(agreeing)
(MISAKI gasps)
[AOI]
(gasp) This one's not
getting away from me!
Nagisa's been drilling
volleyball into me for years!
Hyaaaa!
Careful, Aoi!
Wow, That was some
nice control.
Dammit!
[MISAKI, thinking]
Aoi... is trying so hard!
He's taking this so seriously...
and Usui's just toying with us!
[MISAKI, thinking]
That guy is constantly pissing
me off, but... he's always come
through for me when it counts!
[MISAKI, thinking]
I actually believed...
that he was a good guy!
[MISAKI, thinking]
I've never been this angry
before in my life!
Usui, why did you
become my enemy?!
(awkward laughing) Uh, whoopsy.
Did I... just say that out loud?
[USUI]
You sure are a
selfish one, Misa.
[USUI]
You don't want me
to be your enemy?
Are you saying you want me?
[MISAKI]
(stammering) Y‐you idiot! Who
said anything like that‐?!
[USUI]
I see. Well, here goes.
[AOI]
Whoa, where are you aiming?!
[MAN]
Forget it. The wind's blown it.
I won't lose! Hyaa!
He got it?!
[MAN]
It's no good. This
time, it's impossible.
(ALL gasp) Huh?
[MISAKI]
I WILL make it!
Don't, Misa!
(gasping)
YES! Uh?
(gasp)
Look out!
(bracing herself)
(grunting)
[SATSUKI]
Huh?
(USUI groans)
(MISAKI gasps)
[JUDGE]
Whooooaaa!
[USUI] Hmph.
(CROWD murmuring)
[in unison]
Are you okay?
I'm fine, thanks.
There's no way you're fine!
Look at that huge bruise!
That hit you right on
the shoulder!
[SATSUKI]
You have to get that
looked at right away!
Well... That got blown
way out of proportion.
Hey, Usui! You shouldn't
be moving around yet!
And you shouldn't
worry so much.
But I... I mean, it's my fault
it happened in the first place,
so of course I'm going to worry.
So, now you're following
me around because you feel
guilty about it?
Shouldn't you be at
the festival celebrating
your victory?
There's nothing to
celebrate about,
the only reason we won
was because our opponent
got injured.
Who would be
happy about that?
With the way I feel right
now, I'd just ruin any fun
they're trying to have.
Guess it's a good thing
the others are there to
celebrate for us then.
Then I, Erika, shall be
the acting princess!
Just leave it to me!
Hey! What do you think
you're doing‐ the only
princess is me!
Jeez, I wanna be
a princess, too!
You know, Aoi.
You've shown me... just how
much of a man you really are.
Congratulations on your win.
Aunt Nagisa...
[USUI]
But Misa, you really are
reckless, aren't you?
But I guess, I've come to
expect that from you by now.
Usui... I'm sorry.
[USUI] I don't forgive you.
(MISAKI gasps)
What would you do...
if I said that?
(MISAKI gasps)
(USUI chuckling)
You're making fun of me again?!
Anyway, this is all because you
entered the stupid tournament!
[MISAKI] And you knew how Aoi
felt and you still‐!
[USUI] I‐I didn't like it.
You being the Beach Princess,
putting on clothes that would
make guys stare at you,
having your picture taken with
them while they thought dirty
thoughts about you...
I just didn't want to see you
like that, Ayuzawa, that's all.
[MISAKI]
That's... all?
[USUI]
What do you mean?
My dignity was your only reason
for trying so hard to win?
Yes.
THAT'S all it was?
Aoi's situation is way more
important than something that.
[USUI]
To me, THIS is more important.
You still don't get it?
G‐get what? You're always
playing around,
so how could I "get" any‐
[USUI]
Fine. Then look at me.
Right now... I'm not
playing around.
Usui...
Fireworks!
Oh yeah. They're supposed
close the festival with a
fireworks display.
(pouting)
[USUI]
You're hot.
Th‐that's just because
I got sunburned!
Yeah, yeah.
[MISAKI]
Grr, enough! Let's
hurry and go back!
[USUI]
(chuckling) Yeah, I get it.
Oh, look, the couple's
finally back.
[ALL]
Welcome back!
Aoi! What's all this?
Sure enough, no one could
possibly make a better
princess than ME! Hello!
I see that...
By the end of the night,
it was more like
the Aoi Festival.
Get this! Gon‐chan and Sayu
entered the tournament, too‐
they were here
the whole time!
Well, I was invited here
by some visiting relatives,
and then we ran
into you guys...
Yeah, I'm actually here on a
trip with my family, as well.
[GON‐CHAN]
My elementary‐school nephew kept
saying, "I wanna enter!"
[SAYU] Yeah! Mine did too!
We lost before we could play
Misa and everyone else, though.
(giggling)
You guys should have told
us you were gonna be here!
Anyway, now that everyone's back
together again... time for the
real fun to start.
[MISAKI] What kind of fun?
[SATSUKI]Tomorrow's the last day
of our vacation, so we should
all take a photo together!
Everyone, scooch closer
together, more toward the
center.
Is this good enough, Manager?
Jeez, I got tired of waiting for
the idiot couple to get back.
I‐I'm sorry. Hey, wait,
quit calling us a couple!
(click)
Okay, the timer's set!
I'm sure you were continuing
where you left off when
I found you on the trail
the other night.
No! W‐We weren't!
Hmph! There was a bit of
hesitation in that denial!
No, there wasn't‐ and
don't encourage him!
[MISAKI, voiceover]
Slowly, new feelings were
starting to blossom...
(click, flash)
[MISAKI]
And just like that,
summer had come and gone.
(dog howling)
Misa STILL isn't back?!
No it's not true,
it can't be!
To think, our bittersweet summer
has already come to an end!
[TRIO]
Misa! Come back!
[MISAKI'S GHOST]
Shouldn't you go home and
do your summer homework?
This story of summer is
finished. Skip, skip. Ah‐haha...
[MISAKI]
I'm home!
[SUZUNA]
Welcome back, Sis.
Hurry and eat this.
[MISAKI]
Whoa! What's with all
this watermelon?!
[SUZUNA]
I won them, of course.
[MISAKI]
We've had watermelons and the
beach and other summer‐like
things, huh?
[USUI]
The story of summer is now over!
Next time, DANGER shall approach
Maid Latte.
[MISAKI]
Uh! Miyabigaoka's student vice
president is‐!
[SHIROKAWA]
Oh‐ho! I've overheard! Next time
I, Shiroyan, will be making an
appearance!
Let's go, Kurotatsu and Ikkun!
[KUROSAKI]
Aren't you treating us a bit too
much like your henchmen?
[SARASHINA]
Which of us Henchman
is Number 1?
[MISAKI]
Just be whichever
one you want...