[SUZUNA]
Yes, yes.
Oh. Hmm. I see.
Is something the matter, Misaki?
No, I'm just observing.
Go back to what you were doing.
Very well. If you don't mind,
I shall resume.
Where did all of these
magazines come from?!
There's no need raise
such a fuss about it.
I didn't buy them,
I borrowed them.
I bought the postcards
with funds from my club.
Oh. Your Sweepstakes
Club, right?
Would you like something, too?
There's a supplement set,
an assortment of canned salmon,
or a special Swiss Army Knife?
I should've known better.
There's no way I can use
her as a reference.
Reference for what?
From a maid to
a younger sister...
What is that even
supposed to mean?
A little sister is a bundle
of playful and cute!
A‐a "bundle"...?
That's right! It's exactly
the kind of character
our customers have been craving!
Misa, you have to do it,
you'd be perfect I just know it!
It's better if you
style your hair
like you did when
you were younger.
Yeah, I think you need to
wear pigtails or something.
[SATSUKI]
When talking to customers,
instead of calling them
"Master,"
call them "Big Brother"
or "Big Sister."
But you can change it
to fit your character,
like "Big Bro" and "Big Sis"!
[SATSUKI]
Oh! It looks even better
than I imagined!
So, what nickname are you
going to use, Misa?
Huh?
What are you going to
call the customers?
I always call them,
"Big Brother!"
Uh how about "Dude"?
What are you saying, Misa?
You have to say something like
"Big Brother", you hear me?!
B‐Big Brother?!
Big Brother, can you
help me change?
Like that!
Big Brother, can I
sleep with you?
Like that!
You have to say
something like that!
I'm not a
five‐year old!
That's Honoka for you.
She's like an expert when it
comes to the little sister type.
It's like a switch got
flipped, or something!
Now, give it a try!
You're a younger sister,
anxiously awaiting the return
of her beloved older brother!
Repeat after me:
"Big Brother,
where are you?"
Big... Brother...
where are you?
Ah! That's him at the door!
Th‐that's him at the door...
Welcome home, Big Brother!
Welcome home, Big Brother...
I‐I told you! That just doesn't
fit my personality at all...
This is just too much
for me to handle.
It's too much for you to handle?
If you ask me that sounds like
a lame excuse for not
doing your job.
Hey, Honoka!
I have been waiting for
too long to say this.
But I don't care
how hard she works,
or how much the customers
love her ditzy persona,
or the fact that she doesn't
know much about our industry‐
but if she was hired
to do this job,
then she should be able to do
what's expected of her.
Uh oh! Black Honoka's appeared!
Now no one can stop her!
Using your personality and
your pride as an excuse
to avoid doing something
you don't want to do
is the height of stupidity.
Why don't you quit acting
so spoiled, little girl?
[SATSUKI]
Misa!
Wait! Wait!
Don't pay attention
to her, Misa.
If it's too much we can
change your shift!
I know you'll do
better next time.
Oh, that's right!
Lookie! The next event is
a Maid Power Ranger Day!
I said that I wanted
to be the pink one,
but then Honoka said SHE
wanted to be the pink one,
and now she won't
back down!
What color do
you want, Misa?
Any color's fine with me.
Calling it a day already?
Usui!
Oh, you're the guy that
always comes to see Misa!
Your name's Usui, right?
Oh! You'd know, wouldn't you?
What color
suits Misa the best?
What color would...?
We're doing a Maid
Power Ranger event next!
What color do you think
would suit our Misa best?
"Maid Power Rangers"?
Personally, I think she's a
light purple or light blue,
but then there'd be overlap
with the other girls...
I was thinking multi‐colored
vinyl maid outfits‐
what do you say?
Something see‐through, I think.
Oh, hell no!
Now, now.
You don't have to
decide right away.
But would you think about
it for me, pretty please?!
[MISAKI]
Younger sister... cute...
younger sister... cute...
[BOY]
Yo, man, check this out!
[OTHER BOY]
Oh, man, are those real?!
CONFISCATED!
[KUROSAKI]
Huh? A message to Misa in
the Maid Latte guest book?
[SHIROKAWA]
Forget it, Ikkun.
She's not gonna write back
to you in that thing.
[SARASHINA]
I won't know unless I try!
I'm tellin' you, man, you're
never gonna get a reply.
If someone saw that,
they're recognize her
handwriting right away.
There's no way she'd
leave any obvious
evidence like that‐
But what if it's something
overflowing with love...?!
What's with you, Ikkun?
You have some secret plan
to get her attention?
How about...
something like this.
It's a message‐
WITH A PICTURE.
[BOTH]
I‐it's beautiful!
What the hell, Ikkun?
I didn't know you
were so talented!
Well... I've been keeping it
a secret until now,
but the truth is,
I'm actually a closet nerd.
[BOTH]
Ikkun, what the‐?!
But it's not like...
we're any different...
Yes, I said it!
Ah!
Huh? It's decent enough,
so I'll forgive it.
I've been forgiven!
For what?
So, about this...
What color would the flower be?
Huh?
F‐flower?
Color?
What are you talking‐?
Question:
If you had to pick a color
that would best describe Misa,
what would it be?
You have 10 seconds. Ten, nine,
eight‐seven‐six‐five‐four‐three‐
two‐one...
I‐it has to definitely be red!
RED gives a sense of passion
and womanly strength!
Also, it stands out
against Misa's dark hair!
I say PURPLE has a sense of both
aloofness and seductiveness!
It's mature with
a hint of sexy!
It's gotta be black.
BLACK is the only color
for that tight body!
Add in a little lace, and...!
[SHIROKAWA]
In that case, I'd go with
strawberry‐pattered underwear.
[SARASHINA]
When the heck did we start
talking about underwear...?
[UTSUMI]
Hey, check it out.
It's a "little sister"
special edition.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
The president confiscated
that earlier today.
She'll get mad
if she sees.
Yeah, but look!
Doesn't this chick look like
Yukimura's sister?
No way, is it really her?!
What the‐ it's just
a stupid drawing!
[UTSUMI]
But it looks just like her!
Right, Yukimura?
[YUKIMURA]]
Uh, I don't know.
I'm not interested
in that 2D stuff.
It all looks
the same to me.
Really? Pretty much
anything does it for me.
Doesn't beat
a real girl though.
Hey, Yukimura, does
your sister wear
frilly stuff like this?
[YUKIMURA]
Of course she doesn't!
[HAGIMOTO]
Still, it'd be nice,
wouldn't it?
Having a cute, comforting girl
like that at your side...
[YUKIMURA]
You're getting
way too into this!
[HAGIMOTO]
Oops, looks like club's
about to start‐ gotta go!
Well, Yukimura,
I'm gonna, uh...
I'm gonna do
something now‐ bye!
[BOYS]
See ya!
[MISAKI]
Yukimura.
Yes?!
(Screams in terror)
You...
I mean... you and...
your sister...
what kind of things...
What kind of things
do you talk about?!
Just normal things,
I guess...
Then what about her
is "comforting"?!
C‐comforting...?
Is she that really much
like the anime character
in the magazine?!
I‐I...
I think I'm gonna wet myself,
so please excuse me!
[USUI]
President?
Agh! I was s‐s‐simply
doing some research
the best way to address these
confiscated articles...
Oh, it's just you, Usui.
(sigh)
Well? What were
you "researching"?
None of your business!
Siblings?
Yes, I do.
Have I not mentioned it?
I have an older brother
and a younger sister.
Misaki, get this!
Shizuko, her brother,
AND her sister...
all have the
exact same glasses!
No, they're different,
they only LOOK similar.
And they all have
the EXACT same face!
That I cannot deny.
But we all have
different glasses.
So you have
an older brother?
Is something the matter?
Uh, no...
It's just, uh,
I don't have any brothers,
so I was wondering
what it's like.
D‐do you get along?
Do I get along
with my brother?
Well, it's not that we
don't get along...
That's because they're all
just like each other!
Just what exactly is
that supposed to mean?
(Giggling)
What about you, Sakura?
I've got an older sister.
And we get along SUPER well!
We go shopping together
all the time!
[MISAKI THINKING]
I see. Both Shizuko and
Sakura are younger sisters.
[SAKURA]
Let's all go
shopping together!
[MISAKI]
Sure enough, watching them
interact is somehow soothing.
[SAKURA]
I can't. I don't have
any allowance left.
[MISAKI]
But I don't think it's
just because they're
younger sisters...
Maybe the boss is trying to
make a place where people
feel at ease like this...
Misaki?
What is it?
You're staring at us.
Nothing. I was just thinking
how cute the two of you are.
Ah!
Oh!
Wh‐what's gotten into you?
Are you confessing your
forbidden love for us?
Wow, I'm gonna fall
in love with you, Misaki!
[MISAKI]
I have to re‐think this...
Can I really do it?
You sure about this, Ikkun?
You're really gonna draw it?
You know it! I've got
all 24 colors ready to go!
Don't tell me
you're going to‐!
[SARASHINA]
Yes‐ PURPLE!
[SHIROKAWA]
This is a bad idea.
[KUROSAKI]
If you HAVE to draw it,
forget about the colors!
Just do black lace!
[SHIROKAWA]
No, if he's going to do
anything it's going to
be a strawberry print!
[KUROSAKI]
Fine, we go with the
middleground: leopard print.
[SHIROKAWA]
What kind of
middleground is that?
Apologies for the wait, Masters.
Here's a special Cutesy‐Cutesy
Rice Omelette, on the house!
[SARASHINA]
Catter‐what...?
[KUROSAKI]
C‐catter wall...?
[SUBARU]
Seriously...
She's an admirably hard worker.
I've even seen her reading
textbooks on her break
while working out with
dumbells at the same time.
In any case, she's got
her act together, huh?
She's caught on
pretty quickly.
To be honest, I totally
hated her from day one!
I didn't give a damn what her
home life was like at all,
and the special treatment she
got really pissed me off.
But she lifts
heavy stuff for me,
and if I happen to get stuck
with a crappy customer,
for instance...
[MISAKI]
Master, please don't
be too hard on her.
The customers buy it
every single time!
She certainly serves her purpose
every now and then.
She's almost useful!
(Awkward laugh) Honoka,
I'd hate to be on your bad side.
What're you staring at?!
I'm observing.
To see what color you are.
I told you to just pick
whatever you want!
As long as it's
not see‐through.
Don't you think you're
putting a little too much
thought into all of this?
Shut it.
You have a younger sister,
don't you?
Why don't you just imagine
what she would say.
She would never say "Big
Brother" or anything like that!
And I'd never used a cutesy
voice like that in my life.
[USUI]
If you can't do it,
why not just change shifts?
Or take the day off?
[HONOKA]
Why don't you quit acting
so spoiled, little girl?
[MISAKI]
Saying "I can't do it"...
It's just a lame excuse!
Also, Maid Latta isn't some
normal coffee shop.
It's a place where you can
go have fun and experience
something unexpected and great.
Not to mention, they have
their own special atmosphere,
one that the staff has created
through hardwork and devotion.
I've finally noticed that.
That's why I'll become
this character‐
Why are you so concerned
about it now, though?
Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?!
I think you're fine
the way you are.
If you suddenly became
my younger sister...
What are you...?
That'd be...
so hot.
I'd make a collectors album
titled "365 Days of Misaki's
Sleeping Faces,"
and have a different angle
for every day of the week.
Ah! Stay away from me,
you freak!
(Giggle)
Welcome home, Big Brother!
[GIRLS]
Oh!
It's not perfect,
but it's still pretty good!
[MISAKI]
You must be tired after a long
day at work. Come sit down!
It sounds a little rehearsed,
but I think that overall she
passed with flying colors!
We'll practice with her a
bit more and she'll be perfect!
I admit she's worked hard,
but it seems she went for
the obvious Lolita‐type.
She could just as easily have
gone with another type,
such as the diligent,
prim‐and‐proper character,
but it seems she
really had no idea.
(Giggles)
Welcome home, Big Brother!
Uh‐uh‐oh...
Wh‐what's wrong?
What do you mean,
what's wrong with you?
I... uh...
Your calling me "Big Brother"
is freaking me out.
What's with the act
all of a sudden? It's weird.
Are you trying to
get something out of me?
Or are you feeling guilty
about something?
Uh...
C‐come on, Big Brother!
Misa's always like this‐
Are you trying to make up
for farting in front
of me the other day?
Ah!
[SATSUKI]
No, Misa!
What an amateur,
getting mad at
a customer's joke.
Well, it was a pretty bad joke.
G‐geez, Big Brother! What ever
am I going to do with you?
Here, have some WATER!
Where's this water from?
Your "brother" only drinks
water fresh from the Alps.
Go get me some.
There you go again,
making jokes.
You really got me
this time, Big Brother!
Anyway, what would you
like today?
I recommend the
cutesy‐cutesy rice omelette‐
"Big Brother" would like
roast lobster in a
white wine reduction,
foie gras poêlé,
a side of summer truffles,
and a bottle of your
finest champagne.
Another joke! You sure are
picking on me alot today‐
Cut it out already,
Big Brother!
Aren't you the one
who should cut it out?
If you're getting picked on
it's because you're
putting on this weird act.
You even lied about
farting in front of me.
I told you I didn't do that!
You idiot perverted
older brother!
Whoops‐
she finally lost it.
Well, Misa, you seem like
you're in a bad mood today.
I guess I'll just leave.
B‐Big Brother...
Please... please come back and
see me again sometime, 'kay.
This... this is...!
It can't be!
Another type of "little sister"!
It's THAT!
Yes! It's not Lolita OR
prim‐and‐proper, it's...!
The air‐headed...
hot‐and‐cold younger sister!
Good work, everyone!
Honestly, I never expected her
to put that much work into it.
Huh? But Misa's a
hard worker to begin with.
Next time I want to see
more of her cute "hot" side.
I agree! We already see more
than enough of her "cold" side.
But, I don't think she's
suited for these events.
Because Misa's at her
absolute cutest when she's
with you‐know‐who...!
Aren't you gonna
say "thank you"?
For what?
You succeeded
because of me, right?
I wouldn't call that a success.
I guess I don't have
what it takes after all.
When I throw myself into a part
I lose my ability to make
clear judgments,
and I lose my temper, I guess.
That's why you
shouldn't try to play
some fake character.
Just be yourself.
But my personality isn't
"comforting" at all!
Really? I think
you'd make a great
little sister.
Shut up, stupid Usui!
[SATSUKI]
Misa's at her best
when Usui's by her side.
[GIRL]
Oh, look!
Upperclassman Usui showed up.
Best of luck!
Uh‐hm.
Do you need something?
Um, yes! I'm sorry for
calling you out here.
U‐um, but, there's something I
wanted to tell you in person...!
The truth is,
since the moment
I saw you,
I was in love...
[USUI]
Oh...
W‐will you please
be my boyfriend?!
That was close...
Upperclassman... Usui?
I'm a huge freak who likes
maids more than anything
else in the world.
All my favorites books are about
maids, I visit maid cafes
every single day,
and I collect
maid figurines, too.
My heart races every time
I play maid dating games,
and in my spare time
I dress in a maid costumes
and breathe heavily while
I stare at myself in a mirror.
See ya.
Huh...?
Don't give up!
He's just testing you!
There's no way that's true!
I don't care about that! I...
If you just give me a chance,
I can become your type!
Sorry, but I don't think so.
Usui! The nesxt class
is about to start.
Miss President...
Strip.
What are you...
...saying, you pervert?!
[USUI]
You planned on waiting
until your next break,
even though it's this bad?
[Masaki]
It's not like I'm
bleeding or anything.
That's our president for you,
rugged till the end.
Anyway... how did you
even know about that
to begin with?
Are you stalking me now?
Don't blame it on me.
You're the one who
always seems to be around
no matter where I go.
It's fate.
Besides, if anyone should be
surprised, it should be me.
Every time I see you at school,
you're always standing up
for the girls and
beating up the guys.
You're like the
main character of some
sort of romantic anime.
Well excuse me for not
being more ladylike!
And what's wrong with a woman
protecting other women?
I didn't say it was wrong,
did I?
But...
Seeing you risk yourself for
a guy was pretty unexpected.
I didn't have a choice.
I couldn't just let him
get hurt like that, could I?
So you're saying you'd
help out both guys and girls,
even if you put
yourself at risk?
I'd do that for anyone.
I'd even save YOU
if I had to, Usui.
I look forward to
seeing that, Misa!
Er! Quit making fun of me!
Oh, no! Misa,
what happened to your arm?!
[MISAKI] It's not a big deal.
[SATSUKI] It's all wrapped up
in a bandage! Are you all right?
It looks worse than it is,
don't worry, I'm fine I promise!
You sure about that?
It was pretty swollen.
Usui! Boys aren't
allowed back here!
I'm about to start my shift
anyway, so hurry up
and leave already!
Roger that.
All right, ma'am,
I'll be going.
Let me know right away if it
starts hurting, okay, Misa?
Well, guess I'll
take it from here!
Don't worry, Usui,
she's in good hands,
so just leave her to me!
Yeah. But watch out,
she's the kind of person
who puts on a brave face
and doesn't like to
take help from others.
So make sure you're discreet
or she'll catch on.
(Satsuki giggles)
Oh, no! Where'd all these
flowers come from?
It's a lot of trouble for you,
isn't it, Usui?
Not really. I'm enjoying myself,
so it's no trouble at all.
Is that so?
I guess it would be kinda fun
just to watch someone who's as
hard of a worker as Misa is.
She puts her all into
everything she does,
and even though sometimes
she can't do what she
sets her mind to,
she pushes herself to
her absolute limit
and then you end up getting
worried about her, right?
(Misaki wheezing)
One day I WILL overtake you!
[SATSUKI]
Not only is she a splendid
and capable young lady,
but she's so determined
to get better
that it makes it hard to
take your eyes off her.
It's like,
she gives you power,
and the drive to say,
"I can do better, too!"
That's what you enjoy
the most, right, Usui?
Hm.
By the way, I thought about
what Misa's color should be.
Ah!
Someone like her can't
just be a single color.
So that's why she's...
Definitely white.
Huh. I didn't expect that.
Geez, Usui, what're you
still here for?!
I told you to
hurry up and leave!
But it's also...
The type of color that
takes on other colors, too.
[MISAKI]
What are you
talking about?
[SATSUKI] Cute overload!
Ah, now you're red.
Oh no‐ it's a cutesy
flower overload!
So cool! White Misa's the best!
Defeat me with your love!
(Grunts)
Us, too! Us, too!
All right then, who's next?
Uh, actually, I'm starting
to have second thoughts.
Me, too.
[SATSUKI]
Oh, no! I STILL can't
hold back the cutesy flowers!
[MISAKI]
Ma'am, it's really a shame
to have this event just once.
[SATSUKI]
We'll do it again sometime!
Look forward to
Younger Sister Day Part II!
[USUI]
Use something transparent
and revealing.
[MISAKI]
Quit saying that!
Just shut up, Usui.
Say, ma'am, are you a
younger sister, too?
[SATSUKI]
Yes! I have an older brother.
[HONOKA]
Manager! A cute girl
decked out in frilly clothes
just walked into the café!
[MISAKI]
You're right.
[SATSUKI]
She's here!
[USUI]
Misa, you're sooo cute.
[MISAKI]
Usui, just shut up.