You'll never kill
us all, Claymore...
You shouldn't be out here.
It's too dangerous.
Get back inside and I'll let
you know when it's safe again.
Come on.
A winged Yoma.
The job is finished.
A man will stop by later
to collect the money.
You'll give it to him.
Wait!
Clare.
Wouldn't it be a good idea if
you took just some of the money
for yourself?
A representative from the
Organization is the one
who collects the money.
Why?
Is there something you need?
No but...
what happens if you
have an emergency...?
Or if you need new clothes,
like you do right now?
The Organization will
bring me new clothes soon...
Just like they do
when money is needed.
So do all of the Claymores
work for someone in particular?
We've been a part
of the Organization
since we were very young.
Really?
How young?
That's irrelevant...
Age differs for us...
We cease the aging process
once are infected with Yoma
and become a Claymore
within the Organization...
Claymores are half Yoma...
Which means Clare
is half Yoma...
But she's still human too.
Half human, half monster.
Hold on...
Are you becoming hungry?
Yeah...
I mean we haven't eaten
anything since this morning.
Aren't you even
a little hungry?
Can you cook lizard?
Alright...
It should be cooked by now.
Here you go...
--Thanks.
--take it.
It may be ugly but
it sure does smell good.
I wish I had some
of my seasonings...
oh, well.
Clare...?
What's wrong?
Do you not like my cooking?
No...
it tasted good...
It's just that I'm
already full, that's all.
Wait, how can you be full...?
You only took
a couple of small bites.
It has to do with
the way our bodies work...
A small amount of food
eaten every two days or so
is sufficient for us...
It's not uncommon for
Claymores to go a week
without any food
or water intake.
A whole week?
Watching you eat
like that is invigorating.
When your appetite is
non-existent you tend to
not enjoy the act
of eating all that much.
Well...
that just means
more for me, right?
I suppose...
Food is a luxury
reserved for humans.
Sorry...
why did you become a Claymore?
Joining with the Organization
was my only option.
Huh.
Is it hard to become one?
Yes.
Then why would you...
I guess I shouldn't
be prying like this...
But she seems so lonely.
I wonder if she has
a family or any friends.
What's that...
on your chest?
Once we reach a certain
skill level, we are able
to take on solo assignments
and receive a personal emblem.
It's a unique
representation of our name
and is used to distinguish
us from each other.
So, when was
your emblem given to you?
Where you going?
Don't follow me.
Bathroom break?
Over here.
You're very sweet...
Letting that child tag along...
He'll soon interfere
with your work.
The boy's only a cook...
He won't get in my way.
Your cook, huh...?
You almost sound human
when you talk like that.
Does the boy conjure up
a distant but pleasant memory
from a previous era...?
How sentimental.
Did you bring the change
of clothes I requested?
Turn around.
You're becoming reckless.
The wound may have
healed up this time...
but don't let that blind you to
the fact that you're vulnerable
in certain places
just like anyone.
You are healing up
nicely though...
You shouldn't have
to address it after tonight.
I wonder what the boy would
think if he saw your body...
Try to keep the
conversations to a minimum.
If you let yourself
become attached,
you're the one who will suffer.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I was asked to
give you something...
here it is...
A black card...?
It must be a mistake.
There's no way I could...
Feel free to read it
at your leisure.
Who could it be?
What's taking her so long...?
She must've really had to go.
Hello.
What's wrong...?
Is everything okay?
Hey, look...
I dried all the leftover meat,
so whenever you get hungry
just let me know
and I'll have it ready.
Clare?
Tomorrow we head for Schiele...
We'll leave at dawn so
be ready to move, understood?
Oh...
Sure.
It's gonna be okay...
Just stay with me
and we'll be fine.
Don't cry...
Get out of their way...
Hey is...
that a...
Well I'll be damned.
It's a silver-eyed witch!
Why did she come here?
Did we send for her?
There's no way.
No one's been attacked by a Yoma
within twenty miles of here.
Just seeing her
gives me the creeps.
I don't like this one bit.
I don't care if
they mean well or not,
those witches are trouble.
How rude...
You know if a Yoma had
eaten some of their families
they would all be
begging you to stay.
Yeah?
Uh, good morning!
Do you have any rooms ready?
Well, uhhh...
It's for the boy only...
I won't be staying.
You're not...?
Where you going?
You'll stay here until
I finish my assignment.
I wanna go!
Just wait for me in the room.
Um...
so...
Are you hunting a Yoma here?
When will you be coming back?
Later...
Your village is
clear of any Yoma...
--You have my word.
--Wait...
If there's no Yoma to kill
then why aren't you staying?
Don't worry.
Yeah, right...
You're ditching me,
aren't you?
I'm not.
So, there is
a Yoma after all...
That reminds me,
I saw another Claymore
just outside of town
a few days ago.
On Schiele Mountain?
Uh... yeah.
I'll be back.
Thank God.
But Clare.
Poor boy...
With all the time you've
been spending with a Claymore,
you don't seem to know much.
Huh?
Is it possible you're
not even aware of the fact
that a Claymore is
half-human, half-monster?
I know about that...
But...
Clare is no monster.
She's no human...
They take the flesh and blood
of Yoma into their bodies.
Yoma's flesh and blood?
That's what makes
them mixed-breeds.
They're equal parts
human and Yoma...
Our organization created them
to fight the Yoma epidemic.
But for some unknown
reason they were
only successful
in modifying the women.
You should know that
since you're buddies with one.
Hold on...
You're saying Claymore's
were human to start with?
Who knows?
History isn't clear on that.
Then how do they take
in the flesh and blood
of Yoma and survive?
Survive...? They don't
'survive.' But, they do fight
the Yoma inside themselves
with what little humanity
remains after
their transformation.
That's the reason they remain
an ally to your race.
Before, humans were
helpless against the Yoma,
making Claymores
the ideal weapon.
The ideal weapon?
But there is one fatal flaw
that affects all Claymores.
No matter how much they fight...
they eventually become Yoma.
Huh?
The more power they utilize...
the closer their bodies
inch towards becoming a monster.
Such is the way of things,
I'm afraid.
Those who are no longer
capable of suppressing it
and become Yoma...
are euthanized
by the Organization.
Then...
that means...
Clare will become a Yoma...?
You're lying...
It can't be...
No...
it hurts...
it burns me...
Clare!!!
Raki...?
Didn't I tell you
to stay behind?
Please Clare...
What's the real reason
you're out here - tell me.
You didn't come all the way out
here to become a Yoma, did you?
It was unwise for you
to follow me.
Your safety is in danger...
I've told you -
there is no Yoma here.
However.
There is someone who
has reached their Yoki limit.
Yoki...
I saw another Claymore just
outside of town a few days ago.
It's the other Claymore, right?
Correct...
I'm going to kill her.
Wait you are...?
But she's on your side.
There's no choice.
A Black Card...?
What's it mean?
On the day of our inauguration,
each of us is given a single
black card to store
within our swords.
For every battle we fight,
the line is blurred between
our awareness as humans
and our awareness as Yoma.
In time, we reach the limits
of our human mind...
And transform into
something that we hate...
Yoma.
Then, death is a gift...
a release from this...
curse.
We then send our black card...
to the one person that we would
like the most to kill us.
So then...
Which Claymore is it that
sent you her black card?
She joined the organization
around the same time I did.
We always comforted
each other through the worst
of experiences.
On the path to becoming
mixed-breed warriors...
The pain is utterly
devastating...
We were only able to sleep
while huddled together.
It's gonna be okay...
Just stay with me
and we'll be fine.
It's been too long...
my friend.
Elena.
You haven't changed.
You look the same
as I remember you.
I'm sorry we had to meet
under these conditions.
I wanted to see you.
It's been an eternity, yet it
only seems like yesterday...
Those days were filled
with nothing but pain.
Luckily, the only memories
I still carry with me
are the happy ones we shared.
I actually began
hunting later than you,
but I reached my Yoki limit
sooner and now await my death...
How pitiful of me.
I really believed
the power of Yoma would
bring us greater strength.
But now...
Now I see that the power
of the human heart...
has to be stronger than the Yoma
constantly churning within us.
Uh...
No...
Please Clare...
save me...
Do it quickly...
While my heart is still human
and my soul is my own.
Clare, please don't do it...!
She's your friend!
There has to be another option!
Do it.
Clare.
Don't go...
Clare don't!
Thank you...
my friend.
Now...
I can die as a human being.
Elena and I...
Joined the organization
around the same time.
We always comforted each other
through the worst of it.
She was a skilled warrior.
It's a tragedy that we
were forced to meet again
under such circumstances.
I will always
cherish our memories.
And...
Having joined the Organization
when I was still very young...
Elena was the only friend
I've ever had in my life.
Why...
I just don't get it...!
Why fight Yoma when you have
to endure so much suffering?
Why Clare?
Because...
it's the reason why we exist.
Evil lurks within the shadows.
A darkness so profound,
it swallows the night.
Next time,
The Darkness In Paradise.