I know what your new name is...
It's Clare.
How does that sound?
Clare was one of
the twin goddesses.
She was beautiful,
virtuous, and good.
Your parents probably
wanted you to grow up
with the goddess's traits.
Now let's move.
Come over here...
I want you to see this.
That is Rokut.
We'll be there by tomorrow...
That is where we go
our separate ways...
Now don't be like that...
You'll be happier in that town
than you'll ever be with me.
Please don't be worried.
I won't abandon you
right when we get to town...
We'll find someone there
who will look after you...
I won't leave you until
I know that you're safe.
So rest easy.
So she cried herself to sleep.
What an unusual girl...
All those tears
over leaving me...
I could never be
the family she needs.
I'm sure that whatever family
she ends up with in Rokut...
will give her a far
better life than I ever could.
She'll be fine...
She'll finally have
the life she deserves.
Now then.
So what can I do for you?
I'm...
I'm gonna...
Of course I knew
you were following us...
But if you'd seen to your
injury instead of stalking us
this entire time, your
new stump might not have
gotten so infected.
If you've come to take
your revenge on me,
I suggest you reconsider...
I am forbidden from killing
humans, but I can think
of several other ways
to get rid of you.
I know that you can't kill me...
But I didn't
come here for a fight.
I really came here for this.
I'm glad I found you...
Don't worry, this get
together is gonna be
painful and bloody...
You'll get no pleasure
from raping me.
You saw my body...
Do you really think I care?
This is about your humiliation!
I'll make you live with your
shame like you've forced me
to live with this deformity.
Go ahead then.
It's humans like this one
that I am sworn to protect...
And die for.
Such a superior little smile you
had when you butchered me...
But I think I know a way to wipe
it off of your pretty mouth!
You're so damn sure
of yourself...
But I'll teach you how to
feel like the monster you are!
You little brat!
So you wanna fight?
Now let's say
goodnight, sweetie.
Huh...?
What do you plan on doing
with my sword Claymore?
You had better be careful.
This is a deadly game
you're playing...
It wouldn't be wise
to break your own rule...
You'd be
slaughtered for sure...
Then allow me to enlighten you
about the 'rules,' you idiot...
Whether I choose to
follow a rule or break it
is entirely up to me
and no one else.
I could kill you
where you stand...
then I'd gladly accept the
consequences for my actions...
Or you can
vanish from my sight.
Leave this place...
the stink of your wound
is making me feel sick.
Worthless bandit scum.
Are you all right...?
Come on.
Wait, What's wrong?
Clare?
Doesn't it...
it hurt?
So you can...
You can talk?
It looks...
like it hurts you so much.
I see...
You mean this scar...?
It does look bad...
But it doesn't hurt me
as much as it might seem...
Don't worry about me.
But it does hurt you, Teresa...
I know it does because I see it
on your face all the time...
Even when you're smiling, I can
see it still hurting you inside.
Your eyes...
They look just
like my eyes do...
Like you're scared and
alone and you hurt so much
you can't stand it, but you
don't want anyone to know it...
I know...
That was why...
So I was the one that
she was comforting that day.
She didn't cling to me because
I saved her from that Yoma...
But because she knew that we
shared the same kind of pain.
Everything she had was
taken away from her
and she could sense that I had
suffered in the same way.
She could feel our kinship...
even when I couldn't.
She comforted me in a way
that no one in the village
would do for her...
She gave me what she wanted
so badly for herself...
Understanding...
And unconditional love.
The same love that Clare
has never known for herself.
I kicked this tiny
girl over and over...
When all she wanted
was to be held.
She taught me something
I thought I'd never learn...
That even silver eyes like
these can still shed tears.
It looks good on you.
It's all yours.
But it's too-
If you are concerned
about the expense, don't be...
I have too much money
and its rarely spent
on anything worthwhile.
Now then...
Let's go.
Incredible!
That Yoma didn't
even stand a chance!
So that must be a Claymore.
Our village is in your debt.
I wouldn't ever have imagined
that you would rid us of
that monster so quickly.
It's my job...
Save your gratitude.
Rokut is so secluded by the
mountains that we were sure
no one would come out
here to help us...
So...
Please accept this
payment and our thanks
for all of your assistance.
A man dressed in black will
come to retrieve my fee
when I'm gone...
I'm not allowed to accept
the money on my own.
Oh- Whatever you say.
Teresa.
I have a favor to ask you.
This child...
Give her a home in your town.
But...
who is she.
Why is she traveling with you?
Theo was were
I first encountered her...
And she's not a Yoma,
I assure you...
Her parents are both dead and
she has no other family ties.
I hope you'll grant my request
and give this child a home.
Well I'm sure we could find
someone who would be willing
to take her in, after all it's
the least we could do for you.
You are very generous indeed...
thank you.
What's this?
I don't-
I don't need any of this.
I don't want clothes or shoes...
I only want to stay with you.
Let me come with you, Teresa...
Oh, please...
Don't go away and
leave me all alone again!
I want to stay
with you forever!
Just please don't
leave me here please.
But Clare...
You know what my duty is and
why it's far too dangerous
for you to come...
This is the life I lead,
and I can't be responsible
for a young girl...
Why not?
You'd find yourself
in harm's way...
I don't ever want to put
your life in danger...
Please understand...
You and I live
in very different worlds.
Stay here and
live a human life.
I'm glad we met...
I won't ever forget about you.
No...
Don't go...
Please...
no!
Listen, these people can
give you a good life,...
just go.
It simply won't do for a pretty
young girl like yourself
to be walking around town
without a stitch of clothes on,
now will it...?
Come, and we'll find you
something nice to wear.
My thanks to you...
for everything.
She'll be safe here...
And we promise to look
after her as if she were
one of our very own.
I'm sorry...
I wish I could
take you with me...
But, you will find a
childhood among your own kind
that I never
could have provided.
Live as a human...
Grow as a human...
Die a human death.
This is the greatest gift that
I can possibly give to you...
So use it well.
Farewell, Clare.
Oh, no!
What was I thinking...?
I should have known when
I ran into bandits
so deep in the woods...
They've been after
that town from the start!
Tucked away in the mountains,
no one would ever know
if they were under attack.
But with a Yoma living
somewhere inside the town,
the thieves weren't able
to make their move.
That Yoma was the only thing
keeping them at bay.
And then I interfered
and destroyed it.
I'm too late...
Clare!
Kill all of the men...!
And take the women...!
c'mon!
With that Yoma dead and gone,
we can do as we please
without fear of
interference from anyone!
So give thanks to
the half-breed witch...!
We'll come back
for the rest later!
Damn you bastards!
I'll kill you!
How could he...
How could he reach me
from that far aw-
You got to witness
my Falcon Sword...
It's an honor to be
killed with this blade.
Look what I found...
Such a young scent...
Boys, look who we have here?
This is quite the coincidence...
isn't it?
Now that that Yoma
has been destroyed,
it looks like
you're not needed.
And since Claymores know
better than to get involved
in human affairs, what
we're doing here should be
of no concern to you...
So what is it that brings you
before us, Claymore?
Sight seeing...?
It's not like you can do
anything about our fun here...
Think we deserve a spanking?
Clare.
Hey...
So nice to see you.
Did you forget something
the last time you were here?
Finders, keepers...
But don't worry, I promise to
take real good care of her...
I mean, we're already such
good friends, aren't we...?
My new pet.
I love watching the veins in her
neck when she's screaming...
She kept crying,
'Teresa, Teresa!'...
You hurt me, witch...
Now how am I going to
caress your filthy body...?
I'm tired...
Damn you, you rotten bastards.
You are worse than the Yoma
and you all deserve to die
for what you've done.
There will be no survivors...
Each of you dies tonight.
So she's finally lost it...
They'll be coming for your
head now when word gets out
you killed a human!
You'll be slaughtering us...
That could be...
But you shouldn't underestimate
my friends and me...
You aren't the only one
that can handle a weapon.
I don't care that
you're a Claymore...
I wouldn't give a damn if you
were a full-blooded Yoma...
I'm still going
to take off your head!
You're the only one that's ever
deflected my first attack,
which gives me an opportunity
to try out a new move
that I've been working on.
See how well you do with this.
This is what my Falcon Sword
is capable of...
But you can
barely see it, can you?
Where's that pretty
smile of yours now...?
Are you realizing just
how outmatched you are
in this fight?
You can't fight what
you can't see, half-breed.
Do your worst if you even
think you can get close to me.
But I know that your
kind's not made of steel.
So now...
What does the big, bad
Claymore want to do with me?
What the-?
She- she murdered the Boss!
What the hell did we think
we were doing taking on
a monster like her?
I haven't seen anybody move as
fast as that in my entire life!
R-Run!
That thing is a monster!
She's gonna kill us all...!
Get out of here!
Clare, wake up...
You're safe.
Thank you.
I sensed that something
like this might happen.
And it appears that
the day has arrived at last.
The rules allow
for no exceptions.
Even our finest are not
exempt from the consequences
of taking human life.
I'm sorry that
it's come to this...
Teresa of the Faint Smile.
You have betrayed
the Organization-Teresa.
Yes, yes...
get on with it.
You can't do this--
she saved my life!
This is not the
fate I envisioned.
But I am willing to do
what must be done here...
Please would you just
spare me the hypocrisy...?
I disobeyed...
And human lives were lost due
to my lack of control.
Teresa...!
Teresa!
Just tell me one thing first.
As for her...
Who will provide for the girl?
That is no longer
your concern...
She will be dealt with by the
Organization from this point on.
I see...
Thank you.
Why won't they listen...?!
Don't you hurt her...!
Stop!
I can't, Clare...
Goodbye.
Teresa!
The wounds aren't deep.
Your Yoki powers will be more
than enough to close them...
You'll be all right.
Sorry, but...
I'm not quite ready to die.
Teresa!
You're alive!
Never.
Leave.
Me.
please...
please.
There, there...
Stop your crying...
What have you done now...
Teresa?
Only what I have always done...
I've kept myself alive...
The only way I know how.
But it's all different now...
This little girl has
given me a greater purpose
in my life than
I have ever known.
You will regret this.
We'll see.
But not right now.
This new development
is troubling indeed.
For Teresa of the Faint Smile,
the greatest living Claymore,
to desert us-
It is a problem to be handled
just like any other...
The Organization
need not worry.
Please bring Number's two
through five to me immediately.
Teresa must be reckoned with.
Betrayal requires motive...
a price...
and a determined will.
Next time, Marked for Death.