Get out of my way...
I don't waste my time
on weaklings.
Stay where you are...!
You're the only captain left,
we can't afford to lose you...
He killed them all...
And he'll pay for it.
Damn you...
You will die tonight.
All I know is that
somewhere along the way
she lost control and
went over her limit...
It's a fate that is all but
inevitable for a Claymore.
Wait. What did you just say?
Priscilla was a Claymore.
Yes...
And awakening is one of
many cruel eventualities
for their kind.
You son of a bitch.
I'll kill you for this!
The Claymores are doing their
best to keep them back, but...
Even the lowest
ranked ones are there...
But it's hopeless.
What, the lowest
ranked Claymores...?
Wait, are you sure about that?
Clare is there...
I have to go and find her.
We swore we'd live
to see each other again...!
I've kept my end
of the bargain.
This time, I'm going
to protect you!
If I just had more speed...
more power...
I could have saved Flora
and protected Jean...
I need more...! More
speed...! I need more...!
More...! More...! More...!
What...? What the hell...?
What happened?!
Clare!
All I need...
is more.
What's wrong with her?
I don't believe it.
You just appeared out of
nowhere and took my arm off...
I never even saw you coming.
But now...
it's my turn...
You've earned my
undivided attention.
What the hell...
what happened to her legs?!
You allowed only
your lower half to awaken...
If anything, I have to give
you credit for originality.
Clare, no!
I'm worthless...
They need my help...
and I can't even stand.
Damn...
Missing an arm makes
this much more difficult.
I'm sorry were you
looking for this?
You may have awakened...
But I bet regeneration
didn't get any easier.
You bitch.
Clare, behind you!
You think you've got me
beaten just because
you've cut off one measly arm?
What good is being able
to move so fast...
when you don't even have the
skill to maintain control?
When you start moving
it's hard to make even
small changes in direction.
Once you've
committed to your move,
I'll just alter my attack
at the last second...
Your lack of control destroys
any chance your speed
may have given you.
Not to mention-
You forced your lower half
to awaken independently...
That's tricky...
And it's causing a major strain
on the rest of your body.
Damn you!
You'll never win...
You're as weak
as the rest of them.
He's right...
I need more...
I can't defeat him like this!
Whether attacking or defending,
your moves are too extreme...
You've lost your
former precision.
Besides, your pathetic
little body just isn't built
for that kind of abuse...
What makes you think
you can battle against
an Awakened Being and
come out of it alive...?
You're simply not equipped.
Raki should arrive in Pieta
soon if he hasn't already...
I wonder if he's found
the person he's looking for.
If he intends to find her
before she falls to Rigaldo,
he doesn't have much time...
Tell me, Priscilla.
Are you concerned
for his safety?
Don't be...
You'll see your
new friend soon enough.
No.
Don't think I'll fall
for the same trick twice.
You and your friend are both...
dead.
What the -?!
I don't understand...
How does she suddenly have the
power to control her speed?
So strong...
I need more...
He has to die!
I need more!
This one's good.
Watch out, Clare!
Not bad at all.
This could be
quite entertaining...
I can't even remember the last
time I had to fight this hard.
Not since
my battle with Isley...
That was ages ago...
Since then I've fought
nothing but weaklings...
How quickly I forgot.
This sensation...
The fire in my blood!
I finally feel alive again!
All I want-
Is to kill this one!
I am Rigaldo!
On my honor as the
Silver-Eyed Lion King-
I will kill you!
Yes...
The smell of a Yoma...
It certainly takes me back...
The Claymores fighting in
Pieta must be tougher than
the ones I remember.
They've succeeded in forcing
the Silver-Eyed Lion King
to take them seriously.
But still...
Their chances of
surviving are slim.
Begin!
Unbelievable...
I think Clare is
beginning to gain control
over her awakened half.
Damn...
You're kidding me.
There're still civilians here?
What are you trying to do,
get yourself killed?
Let go of me!
If you want to stay alive,
you won't leave this room...
Understand?
Just leave me alone...!
There's someone I have to find
and you can't stop me!
Hold on...
I remember you.
The brat Clare
was traveling with!
I'm not a brat!
My name's Raki and
there's something
I have to take care of!
Whatever it is
you came here for, Raki...
Forget it...
You have to leave
Pieta at once.
But Clare's here.
You mean you came
all this way to see her?
Listen, you can't
handle what Clare
is going through right now.
Leave while you still can!
I won't leave without her...! I
made a promise I have to keep!
Because I promise...
I'll be trying my
hardest to survive...
and come back to you.
Helen.
Fine, I'll go after him.
Is that really Clare...?
I found her!
Her body is
continuing to awaken.
She's awakening?
Yes.
Awakening is one of many cruel
eventualities for their kind.
So unless she can stop...
I can't let that happen...
She can't...
no...
Do you understand now?
There's nothing you
can do to help her...
So just go home.
That's not true...
It can't be!
Mommy...
Daddy...
Brother...
Sister...
I can't let
that happen to her!
Don't you get it...?
Clare needs more help
than you can give her...
You should just go home.
Damn it...
What a pain.
C'mon...
If you're going to stay,
stick with me.
It's not enough...
I need more!
More speed...
More power!
I have to admit you're
better than I thought...
That's too bad.
It's time I ended this!
This is the end.
Good luck using
that speed of yours
while you're holed up in there.
You're out of places
to run...! It's over.
You're head is mine.
That's impossible...!
How did she do that?
No way...
This isn't happening.
You killed my comrades...
My friends!
I feel it...
A new Yoki aura.
What's the matter?
Priscilla?
This still isn't enough
to defeat this monster.
I need more!
Stop, Clare...! You're
pushing yourself too far!
I need more...!
I have...
to have...
more!
She focused her
energy completely
on trying to defeat me...
She even allowed
her legs to awaken...
And in a matter of minutes was
able to learn to control them!
She's amazing!
Unforgettable emotions...
Unimaginable tragedy...
And rage that will not die.
Next Claymore.
"Critical Point, Two."