Promise me...
You'll try to save my
friends...! They're still...
alive...
They're alive.
You better hurry up
and awaken, Jean.
At number nine you might be
the best hope we have.
Fuck you!
If the Creature of the Abyss
doesn't intend to get involved,
then we may still have
a chance of escaping alive...
But in order to do that,
you and I are going to need
the assistance of
the other warrior here.
Get to the lower level
and find Jean...
I can handle things here.
But if she's gone too far-
if she's beyond your help.
Then it's up to you
to take Jean's life.
Damn...
Looks like
I got here too late.
Please...
just kill me.
Hurry up...
and do...
it.
Her body has already
completely awakened by now...
how is it possible she's still
in control of her human mind?
I don't think I can...
suppress it for
too much longer.
Trust me it's the
right thing to do...
It really is...
Now I can die with dignity...
As a human being...
Not as this monster.
Listen...
We have to reverse it.
What are you saying...?
That's impossible...
Once you surpass...
your limit...
there's no turning back...
no matter what.
That's not true!
I've done it before myself!
Even if you surpass your limit,
it doesn't mean you have
no chance of reverting!
I can't do it...
I can't...
Just hurry up...
kill me.
You have to stay with me...!
There's still a chance
you can revert...!
Don't give up!
Revert!
Please...
let me die...
as a human.
I'm human...
amazing.
You're half-awakened...
I don't know how
it works exactly,
but you'll be human for at
least a little while longer.
It almost felt...
like I was being
pulled apart before.
I used the same technique
Galatea used on me...
It's still hard to believe
it actually worked.
We are in desperate need
of your help...
That's why I came down
here for you.
You need me?
No time to talk...
Galatea's approaching
her limit!
I'm currently
ranked number nine...
I'd be happy to help you.
I must say you've done
better than I thought
you were capable of...
I'm so impressed.
You unleashed so much
of your Yoma power...
I thought you were
gonna lose it...
for a second.
And just when I thought
you were about to awaken
you found a way
to fight it off somehow.
I suppose that's
one of the perks
with being so
highly ranked, huh...?
Your control and restraint were
nothing short of brilliant.
Well enough talk.
It's time you were
awakened, don't you think?
Take care of it for me,
will you Dauf?
It's about time...
It took you long enough.
Huh?
Sorry we took so long...
You okay?
No I'm not.
They've worked me
over pretty well...
But I think I'll be
able to manage it.
Oh wow...
I see you got your friend
to revert to her old self...
You three are capable of amazing
things, and I mean that.
I can keep them busy
while you escape...
I owe you at least that much.
Fact of the matter is
you saved my life back there...
Now my life is yours to use
in any way you see fit
so don't hesitate to do so.
While your bravery is noted
and appreciated, Jean...
You wouldn't do much
good all by yourself
in a situation like this.
Our best chance is for
Number Forty-Seven and
I to move in first and
immobilize the creature...
In the meantime you standby
and wait for the right moment
to attack his throat.
Of all the active Warriors,
you have the most powerful
single thrust attack.
Your ability is our strongest
weapon in this fight.
When you do this, make sure
you do it for yourself,
not for us.
So, what now?
Hold nothing back!!
Owwww!
Fascinating.
Attacking from opposite
directions ruins Dauf's focus...
allowing the other one
to use her special technique.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Twenty.
Twenty-one!
Maximum...
rotations...!
My sword will hit
its target square for...
a death blow!
We're ready...!
Do it now Jean!
Look at what you did...!
My fingers...
They're gone!
Looks like we have...
a winner.
That was excellent!
I felt like I was
watching a play!
My hands...!
I now see the importance of
having friends by your side...
I'd give anything to
have the friendship
they all share with each other.
They're broken...!
And it...
it's hurting...
Hey Dauf!
Keep it down, will ya...?
Can't you see I'm trying
to revel in a rare,
sentimental moment over here?
But look at my hands...
They...
They completely destroyed 'em.
Someone with power
as substantial as yours
shouldn't be crying over
a little thing like
healing your hands.
It's like dealing
with an infant.
Oh well then...
I guess we're about done
here for now...
There's no sense in rushing
them to awaken now that
we know what we're...
Why are you
looking at me like that?
Oh I see...
The fight's over.
There's no need to attack me.
I have no intention
of killing you...
My plan was to torture you so
you would awaken, that's all.
Please, you must understand...
All three of you are much more
valuable to me alive than dead.
Hey Jean...
Are you still alive?
I am...
but it's a mir...
...acle.
Do you think you can do that
same attack one more time?
It's not something that
can be done repeatedly...
but if it's
just one more time...
I think I can handle it.
I'm sorry...
but I'm going to have
to ask you to do it again...
I want you...
to put your life...
in my hands right now.
My life...
is already yours.
One more time then.
Why must you people be
so stubborn...?
Oh, Dauf.
Handle them for me.
Just don't kill them.
I will open up
a clear path for us...
Jean...
Come in behind...
and go straight
for his throat!
Let's go!
Take this!
Wow...
Considering her right arm
doesn't belong to her,
she is quite effective.
Stay still!
Damn you!
Although...
She can barely handle
all the Yoma power
that arm has given her.
It's as if she's
at the mercy of
her completely
awakened right arm.
Most of all she wastes energy
with those excessive swings.
Come on, Jean.
What's taking her so long?
Twenty-one.
I'm at maximum rotations.
Take him down now Jean!
Clare, no!
Oh no!
Not again!
Her arm's all twisted up!
Bitch...
You're not gonna
hurt me again.
You die!
Clare!
Put your trust in me,
okay Jean...?
And we will...
get through this.
I already told you...
My life is...
at your full disposal...
I don't care how absurd
your orders may be...
I will do them.
Wow...
She got up from that...
I won't worry too much
there's no way either of them
have enough left in reserves.
They're walking corpses.
Now's our chance
to end this...!
Drive your GreatSword into
that monster's throat!
Idiot...!
Prepare to be crushed!
I need to focus...
Read his Yoki aura so
that my Quick Sword
only reacts to his attacks.
What's that?
Impossible...!
Her right arm is under
her complete control...
Somehow she's
able to attack...
and yet avoid
her friend altogether!
Now I'm mad!
I'm sorry...
This is about all the help
I can give right now.
Do it...!
Now!
I'm gonna take
the bastards head off!
Sorry.
I'd love for you to savor your
moment of victory together,
I really would...
but not today.
Dauf here may
have his flaws...
but at the end of
the day he is mine.
I'm feeling generous...
so I'll count that
as a point on your side.
Sound good to you?
What?
Awww...
You know I was really hoping to
end things before it came down
to a confrontation like this.
My poor Dauf...
I'm sorry to do this to you...
but I can't let you die...
right now, can I...?
Because you're the only one
who can truly accept me...
without breaking into pieces.
Oh right.
I made you a promise,
didn't I?
I believe it was if you could
land a single blow on me,
I would tell you the name
of the man in the north.
A man you should
really be afraid of.
Okay then...
Fair is fair, right...?
All three of you have sacrificed
too much to get this far.
The man that you seek...
Is in the northern
territory of Alfons.
There in a land
frozen in ice.
You will find the
Silver King Isley.
Silver King Isley...
In the land of Alfons...
It's worse than I expected.
If you want to
consider defeating him...
then you must join me...
It's the only way.
Well then Warriors...
We shall meet again.
How could she...
just disappear...
so quickly?
Damn it...
I never imagined the
Creatures of the Abyss
would be so
incredibly powerful.
And look at me...
My abilities are pathetic
compared to those things.
Well now...
That's done...
and I must return to
my original objective.
Number Forty-Seven...
I have been given the
task of returning you
to the Organization.
If you follow me quietly then
we won't have a problem...
You know what will happen...
if you oppose me.
I have no intention of going
back to the Organization.
Not right now...
There's something I need to do
first that's more important
than your task.
So in other words...
you would rather launch yourself
into another battle right now...
And end the day as a corpse.
Jean...
What do you think you're doing?
Trust me this isn't the
way I wanted it to happen
but she saved my
life back there...
I gave her my word that my
life now belongs to her
and I intend to keep it.
You know by doing this you
are defying the Organization.
I've already lost
my life once before...
so the last thing I'll do
is compromise my honor
to extend my time.
Fighters of such a low rank
have zero chance of surviving
a skirmish with a
Creature of the Abyss.
It would be suicide.
And after the creature
pulverizes your bodies
into millions of tiny pieces,
any chance of finding you
will be slim.
In fact it'd be an impossible
job not worth taking on.
The next time we cross paths
it is anyone's guess if
I will embrace you
or strike you down...
Until then I hope
you both survive
and the best of luck
to you, you'll need it.
Stand fast!
I said hold your positions!
Eva!
Kate's gone!
They got her!
Lucia!
A chance encounter,
and another conspiracy...
Signs of a storm lie ahead.
Next time, The Carnage
in the North, Part One.