You see we use "Voracious
Eater" as a code word...
Publicly it's much
easier to explain what
those creatures are by
referring to them as such.
What we're actually
talking about here are
"Awakened Beings."
Miria!
Dammit.
The organization gave us
wrong information...!
We're supposed to be facing just
a normal Voracious Eater...
But a creature like this...!
Do they really expect the
four of us to take on
something of this magnitude?
What is it?
No...
You've gotta be kidding me...
A male Awakened Being?!
Ah, I see you made it Galatea.
You must have summoned me
for a reason Ermita.
What is it?
Near that mountain.
I'm sure you can
sense the Yoma's Yoki
without any difficulty.
But how...?
How could there possibly be
a male Awakened Being?
Here it comes...
Watch yourselves!
Deneve!
That tasted foul.
Helen!
Above you!
He's too fast...!
Get out now!
Behind you!
Just step back forty-seven!
Clare is down!
Damn...!
Stupid idiot...!
She has no skills but
decides to butt in anyway!
That's too many arms...
It's really quite disgusting...
But don't worry, I'll
take care of it for you.
Damn!
You're still alive!
I hope your
rotten flesh is burning...
I thought she was dead...
Her rate of regeneration
is unbelievable!
I can't believe her entire arm
has almost regrown...
Helen's ability to
lengthen her arms
is a very advanced
technique...!
And now, looking at
the design of her armor...
I'm willing to bet her legs
have the same attributes.
Both of their abilities would
normally push a warrior
to the limit of
their Yoki powers...
But these two do it as if
its second nature to them.
I hope its enough to
help defeat this creature...
Oh great,
so you're still here...?
Do us all a favor and
run while you're still alive.
There's no place for you
in this fight.
We're gonna have
to take his head.
We could hack
at his arms all day
and it wouldn't
make any difference.
Tell me...
what are you sensing?
I'm picking up Yoki auras.
One is powerful.
Two are average.
Another is very small
and insignificant...
and the last one
remaining is enormous,
easily surpassing the others.
That's our Awakened Being.
Awakened Being?
Actually, it is a male
awakened being, Galetea.
Did you say a male?
How can we be dealing with
a male Awakened Being...?
I thought they could
only be female fighters who
happened to pass
their Yoki limit.
The Organization is to blame
for these monsters.
In the beginning
they made male warriors ...
I've never heard that...
Claymores...
Yes.
When they first
began making warriors
they were both
male and female...
but over time the males proved
to be complete failures.
That is incorrect.
Our warriors were
not failures at all.
In fact, quite the opposite.
The males were very
valuable assets to us.
When it came to fighting
they were unmatched.
But fighting
wasn't the problem.
The real issue was that
every last one of the males
reached their limit
far too quickly.
You see, awakening is very
similar to sexual pleasure.
The more the males
released their Yoki...
The harder it became
for them to suppress
the overwhelming
urge to awaken.
Unfortunately...
there was no choice but to stop
the production of male warriors.
Let me guess.
After that there was
nothing left for the
male awakened beings to
do but to walk the earth
as Voracious Eaters.
Precisely.
And since the male warriors
were bound to awaken
they only produced
females after that...
I can't believe that none
of you have ever been briefed
on this information.
Not bad but there's one
part of the story that you
neglected to cover.
I left something out?
Indeed...
And frankly I'm surprised you
haven't figured it out yet...
being as clever as you are.
You still haven't figured
out why you specifically
were sent to hunt me down.
Were we all chosen
for a reason?
Seems like there's
something bothering you.
You bastard.
Is something wrong?
I feel a sense of uneasiness
and surprise in the aura's.
Perhaps we should move closer;
it's hard for me to judge
the situation clearly
from this distance.
We can't.
If we move any closer
then they'll know we've
been watching them.
You're the only one
I know of who can sense
Yoki from this distance...
that of course is the
reason you were summoned.
It doesn't seem right somehow.
Alright then...
I believe that now
is as good a time as any.
I think you need a taste...
of the pain true despair
can bring you.
All of you stay back!
Enough!
Bastard!
True despair, as promised...
well, what do you think?
Damn you...
this must stop...
it has to...
You know it's really too bad...
I'm sure that you are one of
the very best claymores.
You are perceptive...
clever...
but a good warrior
needs more than strength.
In order to thrive you must be
intelligent and resourceful.
But then again a warrior
can be too clever...
and if you're not careful
it can also get you killed.
What are you...?
When were you a Claymore?
I am exactly
what you said I was...
I am a monster formed from
a male Claymore years ago...
That's all.
Nothing more, nothing less.
I killed all the warriors
who were delivered to me...
Of course, not without a fight.
I simply do what I must
in order to survive...
I will do what
I must as well...
Excuse me.
Here's your meal.
Please enjoy...
So tell me...
what happened...
to that friend of yours?
Uh...
Well Clare, she had to do
some job up on the mountain.
Up on the mountain...?
I'm sorry son...
there was a group of
Claymores that had to do
something up there
a little while ago...
But unfortunately,
they never came back down.
And no one has heard
any word about them since.
Oh uh...
but I'm sure she's okay...
please make yourself at home.
Clare.
Her stomach is
beginning to regenerate.
The wound is very deep ...
Her chances of survival
are uncertain at this point.
Looks like I'm on my own.
Is this really the time
to be concerning yourself
with their safety...?
It seems to me that it would
be much more practical...
to give me a little
bit of a fight before
I rip you limb from limb.
She's alive.
I will end your existence!
An illusion?
Her back is badly damaged...
Her chance
of survival is minimal...
In this condition...
she's not going to be
much help in this battle.
Now I get it.
Very good.
You can only do it
for a moment.
But you're capable
of incredible speed.
I'm willing to bet that you're
one of the fastest warriors
in the organization,
very impressive Claymore.
Seems you've certainly earned
your single digit ranking.
To the naked eye the
effect looks like a ghost...
which must be why
they gave you that name...
I believe it was Phantom Miria?
It is a great technique...
the question is how long will
work against me, Claymore?
Let's find out together.
Oh my, are you mad?
Charging into your
honorable death!
How heroic!
Die you bitch!
Damn her...
she's good.
I don't get it...
if she could do that all along
why did she wait until now
to pull it out?
More than likely,
her strategy was to wait
and save that move as
a finishing blow on him.
However...
she didn't intend
to use it so soon.
Huh?
You see producing that much Yoki
aura all at once is amazing...
But a technique like that
is bound to take a great toll
on her both
physically and mentally.
If I were her, I would limit
myself as to how many times
I used the technique...
maybe ten times...
or twenty...
but that's the maximum
amount for any battle.
Unfortunately in this current
one she's used it over
thirty times now...
I would be surprised if
she didn't awaken very soon...
Oh what the hell
would you know anyway...?
I'm not going to sit
here and listen to the
lowest ranked warrior!
I got you...
Miria!
It was impressive
how long you lasted...
but in the end
it was a wasted effort...
all I had to do was wait
for you to reach your limit...
and then move in
for the kill.
Now then...
I have the joy of
deciding how I'm going
to torture you to death.
Damn it!
It's no use!
I can't...
I can't make my body move!
This is it...
I now know what he meant...
He promised that he was going to
give us true despair and he has!
Pull it together.
Despair will get us killed...
This battle has
gone on long enough...
This Awakened Being
is powerful...
but, it will not
leave here alive.
Wait...
you're still hurt...
you can't...
But...
impossible...
how can you still be standing
after all of your injuries?
I wondered what that noise was.
It looks like the weakest one
still wants to play with me.
What happened?
What...?
No!
What's going on...?
She's avoiding
all of his attacks!
How is she doing that?
Stay calm.
Hold back your Yoki aura
as much as you can
Be aware of its flow
and it's limits ...
focusing on it will allow you
the greatest perception.
That's it.
Keep your eye on the aura.
Just stay calm
and focused and you can
easily predict his next move.
And here it comes!
She's dodging...
but she's doing it before
he can even make his move.
It's like she knows
what he's going to do!
That's it!
I didn't realize it before!
When we were fighting
she wasn't looking at me
she was watching my aura!
Even in that friendly
fight while we were
both holding back...
she was still looking
for whatever Yoki flow
I was maintaining.
No!
Come on die...!
Die damn you!
when she's facing an opponent
who's more powerful than her...
it becomes much easier
to follow their aura!
And versus this
Awakened Being...
who has no trouble releasing the
full might of his abilities,
she is the ideal fighter!
It can't be...
Is it possible?
Did she develop this skill
for the sole purpose
of defeating Awakened Beings?
What is it?
Something's changed...
interesting.
Is that so?
I don't understand why...
But it's impossible to
gauge how powerful you are.
That's because she moves based
on the aura she's tracking...
the problem is she can't see it
as well when she attacks.
She should practice
switching between modes.
Either that or learn
to read auras while attacking.
Otherwise no matter how
great the technique may be
it's useless on
the battlefield.
Miria!
You're doing well...
but you would benefit
from much more training.
Yes, that is obvious...
painfully obvious.
Wait...
wait a minute...
Let's be reasonable.
I'll tell you anything
you want to know, I swear it.
Careful, he's preparing
for an attack.
I know that.
I am in the single
digits after all.
It's sad.
There are a lot of questions
that I would like to ask you,
but I doubt that you
would tell me the truth.
Here we go...
stay quick and focused.
The same to you.
Damn it...!
This can't happen!
I will not be
destroyed by you!
Impossible.
You're nothing!
The end of one battle...
The beginning of another...
and the fighter's oath...
Next time "Those Who
Rend Asunder Part III"