Clare is not a half-human,
half-Yoma like we are.
She's different.
Implanted inside of her is not
the flesh and blood of a Yoma...
the blood of a fellow Warrior.
And the name of
that warrior is...
Teresa of the Faint Smile.
She fights for the sake
of the person she lost...
and for...
the sake of the person
she doesn't want to lose...
I think that's just
part of being human.
You killed...
her...
Teresa...
Teresa.
Noooo!
Priscilla...
I will kill you!
Clare...
Priscilla...
you will die...! you will die!
Yoma.
I will never forgive you...
Never...!
Not after what
you did to my mommy...
and daddy.
My brother...
and my sister...
I won't forgive you...
I never will!
I'll kill you!
Priscilla.
No...
it can't be her...
It can't be!
God damn Yoma...!
God damn Yoma!
Look out!
Damn Yoma...!
I won't forgive you!
You're gonna die!
By my sword!
You're mine!
Wow...
Not bad.
Clare.
Unbelievable.
Incredible...
How'd she do that?
It's impossible.
They've both gone
beyond our control.
Clare.
Priscilla.
Why...? What's the matter with
them- why are they fighting...?
Just stop.
Clare...
Priscilla...
Please stop!
That all you've got?
Let her go!
Wait a minute...
You're an imposter.
You're not Teresa.
But you have the same scent...
Now...
It's time to die.
I forgot you
don't have wings...
well...
that's too bad.
Now it's time we ended this
charade once and for all.
Teresa.
You killed Teresa...
Clare.
Clare...
Clare!
Please, don't do this...!
Stop it!
Oh my God.
Stop it Clare...
You have to stop fighting!
All this bloodshed...
It has to stop...
Raki...
What's done is done...
Clare...
I know...
I know Priscilla murdered
someone who was
very special to you...
but...
Priscilla's entire family
was slaughtered by Yoma,
just like mine!
And it doesn't stop with us.
Everyone has been affected
by this somehow.
Don't you see...
We shouldn't be
fighting each other,
we're all lucky to be alive...
Please Clare...
I beg you...
Please...! You've got to try and
keep yourself from awakening!
If you kill Priscilla,
then you're no different
than the Yoma!
Please don't do it!
You took her from me...
Teresa...
You...
You killed her.
You killed her!
Clare...!
No!
Raki.
Please...
You can't become a Yoma!
You can fight it.
I know you have it in you!
Her aura just dropped!
Please Clare...
You've gotta be strong!
Don't you remember
the promise we made?
That no matter what
we would meet again.
My promise to you
has kept me alive...
it's the only reason I continued
fighting when I felt weak...
I...
I just wanted to see you again.
I want us to be like we were...
Clare...
I love you with all my heart...
Please don't turn into a Yoma.
Don't leave me all alone.
I promise...
this time I'll protect
you like I should have
from the beginning...
so you can live the rest of
your life as a human being!
...live a human life.
Ra...
ki.
Yes Clare?
I can't...
stop...
it...
There's nothing...
I can do...
Oh no...
Raki!
Jean no!
Jean...
why...?
You didn't run away
this time...
Well done.
Jean...
Why did you...
do this?
It's the opposite...
of what happened before...
Right Clare?
Do you remember that...?
When I had awakened...
you were able to
bring me back to humanity.
We have to reverse it.
Now this is my chance
to return the favor...
I am forever
in your debt Clare.
Revert back...
I know you can do it.
Just like before...
synchronize your
Yoki aura with mine.
Focus Clare...
Focus and I'll pull your
aura back to the good side.
You and I pulled it
off once before...
there's no reason
we can't do it again.
No...
If we do that
you're going to die...
Get away from me...
and save yourself!
It's not too late!
Listen...
These are mortal wounds
I will not recover from...
There's no hope for me...
So at least allow
me to use what's
left of my life to aid you...
I wouldn't want it
any other way.
Jean...
Damn you.
Let's just do it...
Match your Yoki aura!
Jean...
Stop it...! There's no point in
you going through with this...
You don't owe me anything...
Don't sacrifice your
own life for my sake!
Damn it Clare,
I need you to focus!
Don't do it!
Stop!
Clare!
Stop it Jean...
Even if you succeed and
revert me back to a human,
there is nothing in this world
left for me to live for.
If I can't kill Priscilla,
then I may as well die.
Clare!
There will be plenty of time
to find something to live
for once you revert back...
Don't you forget...
There are people in this world
that want to see you live...
And there are those who have
put their faith in you.
The truth is...
I am one of those people.
No...
Just live...
Please Clare.
I'm glad that we were friends.
Jean...
don't die!
No...
Why did you do that?
No Jean...
I haven't been that
entertained in quite a while.
It's you...
I should've known...
Isley
The child's unstable...
though I have no intention
of letting her go yet.
That's why I'm
taking her with me.
I've lost my appetite for
violence after watching
these two go at it.
To continue the bloodshed...
would be uncivilized...
Wouldn't you agree?
Let's leave things as they
are for the time being...
And Raki, I assure you
we will meet again someday.
Keep hold of your sword.
It will serve you well.
His aura...
It was overwhelming.
So that was the Silver King.
God damn...
Everyone's a monster.
Indeed...
That's just how it is...
in this world of ours.
So what happened?
Well Priscilla and Clare
fought and Isley of the North
showed his face before
they both disappeared...
I assume that's all the
explanation that you'll need.
Is she dead?
I can't sense her aura...
That's all I can say
with certainty...
If you want to know...
go see for yourself.
That's true...
I may.
Or at least I would like to...
But it won't happen...
Besides, I already have
my hands full dealing
with the carnage in Pieta.
Good luck to you...
Clare.
Do you think Clare
is going to be okay...?
She was so depressed
it looked like her soul
had been ripped out.
Whether she dies tomorrow
or lives to old age...
it's all in Clare's hands now.
Besides, it's none
of our business.
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
Let's part ways here.
That's a good idea.
Wait...
So what are you
going to do now?
My plan is to leave
the Organization...
and then train hard...
so that I can
have revenge someday.
And I intend to do the same...
I'm determined to reveal all of
the secrets the Organization
has been hiding...
I'll live among the
civilians until
I have sufficient evidence.
That sounds incredibly boring.
Oh...
Have something more
exciting planned?
I'll be damned if I work for
the Organization again...
so...
I don't know.
Well you know you can
always tag along with me.
Sure...
I mean you're not going
to get very far trying
to spar with yourself...
Plus I could use the company.
I guess this is
goodbye my friends.
Though I can't say when...
we'll meet again.
I'm sure.
You better believe it.
Same goes for her.
Don't you forget...
There are people in this world
that want to see you live...
And there are those who
have put their faith in you.
Just live...
Please live.
Something wrong?
I apologize that
it took this long...
to find you.
I'm proud of you
for staying safe.
That couldn't have been easy.
I have no intention of returning
to work for the Organization.
Just know...
The journey will be more
difficult than before.
So...
Will you join me?
Clare.
Of course...
I...
I never want to leave you!
Thank you, Raki.
Teresa...
I'm still alive...
I can almost hear you say,
"That's the way it should be."
Live as a human...
Grow as a human...
Die a human death.
This is the greatest gift that
I can possibly give to you...
So use it well.
Farewell, Clare.