Let me ask you this...
What are the odds that
we'll actually accomplish
our goal here?
This operation...
has absolutely
no chance of success.
And without fail...
I will take the head of the
Awakened Being Priscilla.
What do you say Clare...?
Let's stand together
and survive as a team.
You are among friends here...
Anything you can't do alone,
we'll be right there
to help you with...
So...
don't try to bite off
more than you can chew...
Captain Undine.
You've come face to
face with one of
the Creatures of the Abyss...
so you should know.
The last few days
have been nothing...
If this Isley of the North...
The ultimate Creature of
the Abyss, decides to act,
it will get ugly.
They're coming!
It's time...
Let us head south.
To the town of Pieta.
If everything goes as
planned, it should all be
over with by the
time we arrive.
Are you in Pieta...
Clare?
I can feel them approaching...
They're very different.
Yes...
In their yoki...
their numbers...
their size...
completely different.
The three I sent ahead,
I can no longer sense them.
I assume that means
they didn't survive.
I believe I told you before
that they were never suited
for a reconnaissance
mission of any kind.
If you had just left
the matter in my hands
we could have
avoided their deaths.
What you don't see is
their deaths mean nothing
in the grand scheme of things.
I gave them that mission
because they were expendable.
I never expected much from
them in the first place.
They tested the waters...
I can now say with confidence
that the force in Pieta
is strong enough to defeat
three Awakened Beings...
but can they handle more?
Rigaldo...
you want more
responsibility...
yet you cannot
remain in control,
once your fuse has been lit
there is no stopping you...
Am I wrong?
Silver Eyed Lion King.
I would prefer it if you
didn't call me by that name.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to
dredge up your past...
If the force
assembled in Pieta...
is indeed as strong
as I believe it to be...
all we need to do
is proceed as planned.
Now is the time...
I want you to assemble
the Awakened Beings.
Soon we will secure
the road to the south.
Yes.
The Northern Army...
now at twenty-seven strong...
will totally
annihilate Pieta...
the first town of Alfons.
Once our army is
finished with that town,
not a single hint
of life will remain.
In the name
of the Silver King...
Eradicate all life, down to
the very last rat and insect!
Have we evacuated all citizens?
The townspeople
are safe and sound.
And what's the
status on our injured?
Uma's arm is improving but it
isn't completely healed yet...
There should be enough
mobility for her
to be effective in battle.
That's good.
How many of us will
actually survive this...?
No, I can't think that way...
We'll do whatever it takes.
We will survive!
Pamela!
There they are!
I see them!
Yuliana!
I will make it through this,
no matter what it takes...
I will survive.
What's wrong Isley?
Far away from here, fleeting
lives are being extinguished
one by one.
If only I could see it
with my own eyes.
Come now...
Let's go...
We still have
a long journey ahead of us.
Now!
Captain!
Come on, is that
all you've got...?
I never thought an
Awakened Being could have
the strength of a child!
Damn you!
Now, Deneve, now!
Right!
Twenty-one.
Come back here...!
You two can't run forever!
Where the hell'd she go?
This is taking much longer
than I had anticipated...
We've lost three so far,
but they've only lost five.
Unbelievable...
Our army's power supersedes
anything the Organization
could muster up, yet somehow
they are holding their own.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Five strong warriors...
They must be leading small
squads into battle,
each independent
but working together.
Isley...
Priscilla's gone!
Where is she?
Priscilla...
Priscilla!
It's a monster!!!
There's a monster out there?
Priscilla!
What's that?
Priscilla...
Thank God you're okay,
I was starting to worry...
Uh...
Your clothes...
I brought them for you.
Priscilla...
I...
I'm sorry about that Miria.
There's too many of them...
At this rate
we'll never make it...
--What happened?
--Where did they go?
Did they quit fighting!
What's going on?
What the hell?
So what was that all about?
What is it,
do you sense something?
I think so...
it feels like
someone's coming this way...
Oh no!
Impressive performance...
Here you are in an
impossible situation...
and yet you've come up
with a way to dig yourself
out of sure annihilation.
However I can no longer watch
my forces be destroyed...
without taking matters
into my own hands.
There's...
no way!
It can't be...
Rigaldo!
The Silver-Eyed Lion King!
But why...
Why's he here?
You will be the first!
Veronica, no!
Behind you, Captain!!
You're a quick one.
And you're a strong one too.
But not strong enough.
You bastard!
Goodbye.
Undine!!
She's a Yoma.
Yoma?!
Mommy...
Daddy...
Brother...
Sister...
No...
What are you talking
about...? Your mommy and daddy?
Why are you saying
those things?!
What's wrong with you?
No...
what's happened
to you Priscilla?
Why are you
doing this...? Why...
What's wrong with her...
Isley...
I was wondering where
you'd gone, Priscilla.
Wandering off
whenever you please.
So like you.
You knew about this,
didn't you Isley...?
You knew that
Priscilla was a Yoma!
Not a Yoma.
She's an Awakened Being.
At one time she was human.
Stop it, Priscilla...
You've got to stop
doing that...! Stop!
Please Priscilla...
Don't you see what
you're doing is wrong?
Can't you fight the urge?!
Priscilla...
Please...
Stop, you're just
a little girl!
Don't cry...
Just put it down...
Please Priscilla, stop eating.
It's not right.
It's not right!!
Please...
Priscilla!!
Jean!
Stay back...! Protect Flora!
He's trying to eliminate all
of the team leaders first!
Nineteen.
I've failed you, Captain.
Twenty-one.
My, that's unfortunate.
Jean...
damn you...
You bastard!!!
Scattered light
vanishes into nothing...
and impatience mounts...
Next time on Claymore,
Invasion of Pieta, Part Two.