Someday I'll be strong
enough to help people, too.
Just like Clare...
You took down those
three Yoma quite easily...
excellent.
Well, they really
weren't that difficult.
Amazing work...
I've noticed that
you've been getting
into less trouble lately,
and I believe your manners have
improved immensely, as well...
Something happen to you?
It was during the hunt
for the Awakened Being...
I realized what my
limitations were and was
humbled by the experience.
I have another mission,
if it's not too soon.
I need you to go to the
northern city Gonahl
and hunt down an
Awakened Being there.
Another one?
Unfortunately
it's not Priscilla...
however this one was once
ranked in the single digits,
and is far more powerful than
the male Awakened Being
you were up against.
So you better stay focused
if you want to continue living.
Don't worry.
I won't die...
you can trust me on that.
Isn't that encouraging...
I'm counting on it.
At the rate we're going
we'll be in Gonahl by tomorrow.
I want you to stay here, Raki.
No way!
I wanna go with you!
It's dangerous...
I'd prefer that you stay.
--Yeah, but Clare I---
--You'll stay until I get back.
Alright?
Another warrior is nearby.
I'm sensing something else...
very strange ...
I feel as if every cell in my
being is trying to warn me...
what could it be?
Ah...
Good afternoon.
Are we the first ones?
I was sure the rest
would be here by now.
Actually...
I think we're it.
You mean that...
the two of us
will take it on alone?
You got it...
but the truth is I could have
handled this one by myself.
So I guess you're just a bonus.
She's in the single digits...
but is she one of the top five.
Her emblem...
I'll know for
certain when I see it.
Don't be offended...
but you smell very similar
to an Awakened Being, to me.
Hold on...
I just want to
smell you a bit longer...
you see...
I kind of like it.
Too tight...?
Sorry about that.
Just stay still now...
Course, I'm not really giving
you a choice in the matter,
am I?
Now that tastes strange.
It's odd but it also tastes...
familiar...
you seem to be one of us...
but are you?
Let Clare go!
Now!
Raki!
Stay back, Clare!
I won't let her hurt you,
I promise...
You want her, come get her.
And who is this child...?
One thing's for sure.
He's a brave little human.
Ah, look...
beautiful, isn't it...?
You only see
this exquisite color
when a body is split open...
more lovely than roses,
don't you think?
And how I'll make
that little boy bloom...
oh yes!
She's...
Number four...
Ophelia.
My, my...
Was that fear in your eyes
when you saw my emblem...?
I guess someone's
been talking about me...
you'll have to tell me who.
I really should thank them...
but first...
Let's try something.
Damn!
Well good...
you're faster than I expected.
Why are you doing this...?
Have you forgotten the law...?
If you kill a human
then you have to die...
So what...?
Are you wanting death?
Oh come on now, Clare...
You only die
if you turn yourself in...
Sure they'd chop off your
head if you reported it
but who would do that?
How can you say that?
Of course sometimes
there are loose ends...
like witnesses...
but you can get rid
of those easy enough.
Here's an idea, huh,
let's play a little game!
Now pay attention
while I explain the rules...
So...
The game starts with
me taking on the child...
Of course I won't be doing it
at full strength just yet.
First I'll lower myself
to match him...
And with every passing
minute I'll let myself
get just a notch stronger...
increasing my speed and agility
a little bit at a time.
At a rough guess...
I'd say...
in about ten minutes I'll
have his head in my hands...
all you have to do
is attach your legs
and rescue him in time.
So it's pretty simple.
If you take too long he
dies, but if you rush
getting your legs attached
and they don't work
you can't help him...
Admit it.
That sounds
like fun doesn't it?
Damn you...
Let's start!
Ready?
Go!
This should work if I just
alternate my Yoki aura
between healing
and regenerating.
I'm impressed!
You're actually
better than I thought.
Still room for
improvement though.
Oops, it's been one minute...
Better level up...
That is not the
proper way to hold
a double edged sword, boy...
you should pay attention.
Damn it.
Well, that's not
going to work is it...?
What did I tell you?
If you rush it
they won't stay together
and you'll be of no help.
And does he need help.
But of course if you do
manage to reattach them...
Well...
They won't be
a hundred percent.
Stay calm...
and focus.
Aren't you an
obedient little girl...?
You're doing exactly
what you're told to do.
One!
Two!
Three!
This is so much fun!
I love fighting this child!
Oh, just look at him!
He's trying so hard
not to distract you
that he's not
making a sound...!
No matter what I do
he won't scream
even though he's in
terrible pain...!
Yes...
even though he's soaked
in blood and wants to cry!
Shut your mouth!
You're just saying that
to try and distract her...
Come on. Those attacks
of yours are so weak.
You've barely scratched me.
I've never seen
anything so heroic!
You two are amazing...!
Just fantastic...!
I mean it!
Who do I kill first?
Such a difficult decision.
I don't know whose grieving
will be the most fun to watch!
Well what do we have here?
No...!
Get out of here!
Why would I do that?
Aw...
she's here already...
It's too bad really
because I was so enjoying
playing our little game.
I can't believe my luck.
Two Claymores and a human.
The boy smells intoxicating...
it's so delicious...
Can't help myself.
I'll have to eat him first...
hope you understand.
It's the Awakened Being!
Yes, it does look ferocious...
I hope we can manage.
Come to think of it...
All I really needed was
this young boy over here...
So you two...
Are just in the way.
Oh...
I thought I had destroyed
everyone but the boy.
Yet here you both are.
I must admit...
you are very strong.
They're not healed yet.
Work on your legs!
I'll take care of him...!
You must hurry
we don't have much time!
I know you can do it!
I'm sure you've noticed that's
not an ordinary Awakened Being!
Our only chance is to join
forces if we hope to have
the smallest prayer of
defeating it, now hurry!
I'm...
just kidding.
Clare...
Help!
Rak--
Bitch!
Oops! I guess my hand slipped...
how can you ever
forgive me for this?
Put me down!
Damn it!
Let go of me...!
I said put me down!
Now!
You're so weak you don't stand
a chance of breaking free...
So why even try.
It's a waste of time.
Good thing I got rid
of the kid 'cause
I'll need both
hands for this...
This Awakened Being is terribly
powerful, isn't it, Clare?
There's no one left
to help you now...
sorry.
This can't be it...
This can't be the end...
Come now...
Don't you see - you could
push your power to its limit
and still not come close to me.
So...
it's pointless to struggle.
No...!
I'm not dying today!
Your problem is you don't
know when to give up...
admit it, the human's
as good as dead.
No matter how much Yoma
power you unleash...
You're never going to save him.
The sooner you
accept that, the better.
I'm not going
to give up now...
I have to survive...
so...
I can protect her!
I should have known...
I'm so useless.
Raki!
No!
It's unbelievable!
You would sacrifice everything
to become an Awakened Being
just to save a human...!
For what purpose?
What a foolish cause!
No.
No, my dear!
I definitely saw you
surpass your limit...!
You must be cheating somehow!
And you managed
to attach your legs!
But how?
This makes no sense!
I was under the impression
that if you overextended
your ability there wasn't...!
Wait...
Could it be true...?
You were actually
awakened the whole time!
Oh this is marvelous!
I can not believe this...!
I mean, how often do I get
the chance to kill two
Awakened Beings
in one afternoon?
Raki...
I want you to hang on to me.
Huh?
I need you to hold tight
so that you don't fall...
I'm going to run now ...
You can't let go.
Do it now!
Hold tighter than that.
I'm counting on you...
don't fall off okay?
Come now...
This is foolish.
You can't escape from me.
I think I'll save
the boy for later...
I want to kill you first.
I do hate arrogance.
Arrogance?
And what do you mean by that?
You thought you could
destroy me so easily...
Even said you could take on
two Awakened Beings...
so tell me, do you still
believe you can kill me?
What I believe
is unimportant...
It only matters if
I'm correct, doesn't it?
I need to get as far as I can!
Every step counts!
Well, well, well...
I guess we found out who
the cocky one really is.
Would you like
to beg for your life?
I'm begging you...
stop talking!
Your breath's disgusting!
Now, now, Claymore...
There's no need to forget
your manners, is there?
And now...
for the rest of the party...
Oh dear...
You would think they would
have gotten further than that.
Perhaps my dead friend
here was correct.
She is hopeless.
What happened...?
Impossible...
Your neck...
I broke it.
Oh please.
It would take more than that
to stop someone like me.
If you really wanted to kill me
then you should have cut off
my head like I did yours.
You know...
you're the monster here.
Clare...
So...
the battle is already over.
What now?
We'll go our
separate ways for awhile.
I don't want you
to worry about it...
she'll only be looking for me.
I'm the one she wants.
Now, go.
Raki...
I won't!
I'm not gonna
leave you, you hear me??
You do what I tell you...
Don't you see?
She can track my aura
and hunt me down...
Please go!
I can't...
no...
Let me come!
Please, I only want
to be where you are!
Look, I know I can't really
be of any use to you...
But that doesn't change the fact
that I want to be with you...
I don't care when
I die just so long as
we're together until then!
Don't ever say you
don't care when you die.
Because I promise...
I'll be trying
my hardest to survive...
and come back to you.
You hear?
You will live...
because I won't fail you...
I will find you, Raki.
Promise...?
Promise.
Alright then...
Clare...
I'll go...
And I will survive.
So that...
Someday...
I can protect you...
Good-bye Clare.
Dear God of Robona...
please hear my prayer...
may your blessings
fall on that boy...
Give him your
strength and your mercy...
Until the time comes...
when we're together again.
Ah good...
the stiffness
in my neck is almost gone.
Now that that's all taken
care of I can begin my hunt
for the other one.
Composure is lost
to the ripples...
and for them
tomorrow is shattered...
From the past comes a fighter...
Next time The Endless
Gravestones Part II