Do you need to rest?
No.
I'm fine...
Teresa.
We should be at the next
village some time tomorrow.
Maybe we can relax
for a little while.
Just what in the hell
is up with this town?
Well...
I suppose you could
call it a Yoma's nest.
It seems like any other
village that was attacked
by a large hoard of Yoma.
They had their fun feasting
on the townspeople here,
and then posed as
their human victims...
They've been feeding
regularly ever since.
So...
How many have you taken down
so far today, Sophia?
Let me see...
I believe the last one
makes seven, Noel.
What...?
That's not right.
There are thirteen dead
and seven are mine...
So don't lie.
You only got six
of them and you know it.
Ah, but I think you'll find that
your math is incorrect, Noel...
Seven of those
Yoma belong to me.
Well if you improve your
math skills you'd finally
rise above your rank
as Number Four...
Don't you think?
Dammit, you had better
watch your mouth...
Besides, you're Number Four
and I'm Number Three,
and don't you forget it!
Well...
All force and no style,
just like usual, huh?
You seemed to be handling all
of the unnecessary acrobatics
quite well on your own.
Bitch, if you're
picking fights, I'm ready.
If memory serves,
you started all this, correct.
Well, let's get to it, then...
Why don't we settle
this dispute now?
We'll see who's
the better fighter.
You sure that's a good idea?
You two knock it off.
We came here to kill Yoma,
not each other...
You can bicker all you like
when that's finished.
Am I clear?
So good to see you again...
Ilena.
Well I guess they don't call
you 'Quick Sword Ilena'
for nothing, huh?
I never even saw
the blade move.
I find it equally impressive
that even after slaying
a Yoma at such close
proximity, there's not
a drop of blood on her.
Her rank as Number Two
is unquestioned.
So...
why have they gone through
the trouble of bringing
all of us together?
Sounds like we're
here for something
more important than Yoma.
I'm inclined to
agree with you...
Any one of us could
have easily handled
the Yoma presence here...
It would appear there is
something more important
that warrants this
little gathering.
Care to enlighten us,
fearless leader?
We have a new assignment.
Eliminate Teresa, the
Organization's Number One.
Teresa...?
Wait...
as in Teresa of
the Faint Smile?
And why would we
want to do that?
She's admitted to murdering
a group of humans.
And when she was to
receive her punishment...
she wounded every warrior that
was called to her execution.
You've got to be kidding me.
Teresa is easily the
finest warrior we have...
Why would she betray us...
Instead of accepting her
punishment like she should?
I have no idea...
But the fact that she didn't,
is the reason Numbers Two
through Five have been
called together.
The Organization has ordered
the four of us to make sure
Teresa doesn't
escape her punishment.
Taking down Teresa won't
be easy, so I hope this
Number Five knows her way
around a battlefield...
So, then...
Remind me who the
Number Five is again...?
I have a hard time
keeping track of anyone
outside of the top three.
You really are as dumb
as you look, aren't you?
It's Elda.
Not anymore.
Just like I'm
no longer Number Two.
I've recently been
demoted to Number Three.
Which moves the two of you down
to Numbers Four and Five,
respectively.
What the hell
is that all about?
But then who-?
Number Two just recently
received her emblem...
She was given the
second position ranking
after only months in the field.
A freaking novice?
What makes them think
they can promote some
half-trained rookie to
Number Two ahead of me...?
This is ridiculous!
If the title is what you want,
I'm sure she'll allow you
to fight her for it.
Having seen her in action,
it's not an attempt
I plan to make myself.
Okay, that hurt a little bit.
What is this clumsy little
half-wit think she's doing here?
That's her.
Please allow me to introduce
our newly appointed superior.
Priscilla.
You're kidding me!
It can't actually
be this little brat!
Have you and the Organization
completely lost your damn minds?
This is the new Number Two...
If you're not satisfied,
please feel free to put her
to the test.
A puny snot like her is barely
even worth the trouble,
but if that's what
it's gonna take-
Get up, you little bitch.
Let's figure out who really
deserves this position
right here and now.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me for
being late to the meeting.
I had more trouble with my last
Yoma than I expected, and-
What are you talking about...?
I'm trying to fight you for
your position and you keep
rambling on about
being held up because
of some stupid assignment?
I don't believe
what I'm seeing.
Oh my...
If she was fighting
Yoma so close to us,
we should have been able
to sense her presence.
She can fight the
strongest opponents without
releasing her Yoki power...
The method used by Teresa
of the Faint Smile...
And her hatred for Yoma is
unlike any I've ever seen...
If we are to go up against
Teresa, which I wouldn't
choose to do in a group
of any size, this girl
is our only chance
at success...
Without her, Teresa would
surely slaughter us all.
The child's potential is not
to be underestimated...
In time...
this one will
surpass even Teresa.
Once I reveal what I am,
we won't have any peace
in this town.
And that means another
night of camping instead
of a warm bed to sleep in...
But that's okay with you?
Then here we go.
It's a Claymore!
What's a Claymore doing here?
How frustrating...
I thought we might have
one relaxing night
before we moved on,
but I should have known.
So let's make
this quick, shall we?
Please...!
Please do something
to save that boy!
You Yoma can be
such a nuisance.
There...
Maybe now we can have
a little peace and quiet.
What is all this?
Our deepest thanks
for what you've done!
For what it's worth,
our village will remain
forever in your debt...
Please let us to take up
a collection for your reward.
You're too kind...
A man in black will
come for my fee, and-...
No.
What?
Never mind.
It's okay, son...
You're safe now.
Dad! Dad!
What I did, was really out
of habit and nothing more...
you need not thank me.
But we would be so
grateful for the chance to-
Teresa!
If you insist,
you could arrange for a room
where we can
stay for the night.
We've had a full day
and could use the rest...
Isn't that right, Clare?
Are you still giggling,
you silly girl?
I can't help it...
The look on your
face when everyone
started cheering
and clapping...
It was the first time I'd ever
seen you look surprised.
It certainly wasn't the
response I was expecting...
I've never been openly
appreciated like that before.
But I have to admit
it was a nice experience...
Saving a village from Yoma
without charging a fee.
And for all of them
to be so welcoming to us.
Teresa...
Can I sleep with you tonight?
With two perfectly
good beds here...?
There's no need for us
to squeeze on to one.
Hey.
Well...
Fast asleep before
she even put her head down...
Poor thing.
Rest well...
We'll stay right here
in this town...
At least for a little while.
They're coming...
So...
The Organization has
finally sent some enforcers
to punish me for deserting.
I'll have to
suppress my Yoki aura...
Hold it back to the point
where I can barely feel it.
If I can prevent them
from sensing me,
Clare and I may
be able to escape.
But if they sent experienced
warriors, a simple trick
like this will never work.
Is this it?
It must be.
Well, then...
Teresa sure knows how
to hide with some class.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
But...
But this is too much.
Not really...
That should just about cover all
of the damages to your inn.
The damages?
Hello...
You haven't changed a bit,
my old friend.
We have so much
catching up to do.
I've come here
to take your head...
Teresa.
And do you think you can...?
Ilena?
If you must play
with your Quick Sword...
be mindful of a sleeping child.
How very disappointing...
Appealing to
emotion won't save you.
Don't stop now.
That fancy sword of yours
doesn't work unless it's moving.
Well...
you're definitely better
than you used to be...
There's no doubt about that.
Now let's see.
Uhh...
Can I help you find something?
I think...
it should be right about...
Here!
--Teresa!
--Don't move!
Stay where you are.
Damn.
My, my, my...
How quickly alliances
between us warriors change...
There were four...?
But I couldn't-...
I still can't sense her Yoki!
We have never met, Teresa...
I am Priscilla and the
Organization has given me
my emblem and raised me to
the ranking of Number Two.
Did you say Number Two?
I hope you don't consider
my presence disrespectful,
but I have been sent
to collect your head.
What an idiot.
I'm confused...
It was my understanding that
we were to smoke her out
of hiding and then cut
her down from behind.
But our new friend here
wants us to play fair.
Does she actually think she can
win against the Number One...?
Against Teresa?
Stand back.
Huh...? But why?
I will be just fine, Clare.
There's no need
for you to worry.
Not long ago I swore
that you could trust me...
I promise I'll be okay.
You did say Priscilla,
didn't you?
Well, Priscilla, you could
have easily struck from behind
before I knew you were there...
Mind telling me
why you didn't?
Because that would have been a
coward's attack, Miss Teresa.
By the way...
I have one question
I'd like you to answer.
Tell me why...
Why you failed to
accept your execution
at the appointed time...
I can't imagine what
your reasons must be.
The guidelines the Organization
created help ensure that
we are able to work in peace...
Our rules allow people to
feel safe, and make it easier
for us to make sure
they actually are safe.
But since you broke those rules,
people fear us more than ever!
You single-handedly
destroyed the trust
that took years to develop...
And that is unforgivable.
So...
Leaving me with no choice...
I am forced to act...
your head is mine.
What a pity.
For such an intelligent
young lady to be
so brainwashed by
the Organization...
But...
I'll be happy
to respond to your lecture.
Unfortunately, the real world
isn't always so
black-and-white...
Little Claymore.
Damn.
This girl's not bad.
Look at this...
She's actually
keeping up with Teresa!
Do you know why our
Number One goes by the name
'Teresa of the Faint Smile'?
No.
I always figured it was
because she smiles
whenever she kills a Yoma.
That is not a unique trait.
So why does Teresa go by that
name and not either of you?
I guess I don't know...
Tell me.
You have your agility, Sophia
her incredible strength,
and I have my Quick Sword...
But Teresa doesn't
have one characteristic
that distinguishes her
other than her faint smile.
She may not be known for
anything other than her smile,
but she certainly has
the skills to hold her own.
Not exactly...
Combined the three of us are
far more powerful than Teresa.
However, she possesses
a rare gift that exceeds
all of our tactical abilities.
Huh?
One trait makes Teresa
the most powerful...
Her amazing ability
to sense the Yoki of a Yoma.
Her talent goes beyond
being able to sense
the location of Yoma...
She feels even the
minute flows of Yoki
within the opponents she faces.
In battle, the Yoki flows into
crucial parts of the body
even before they're used.
Teresa can sense
every move that's made.
Priscilla can fight
with her Yoki power
completely suppressed...
Which makes her the perfect
challenger for our Number One.
Look out!
Honestly.
You two are worse
than children.
What a show!
This is one hell of a fight...
I've never seen two
warriors match each other
so evenly before...
I've got to admit that kid
has got some great moves...
Should have been over,
but the rookie's fighting
on equal footing with Teresa...
Wait...
Equal?
It is time.
We must join the fight-
Before Teresa takes
our young friend's head off.
What...? Priscilla's winning...
Weren't we talking
about how much better
she was than
Teresa...? Right...?
Is that right?
When Teresa stops
relying on her senses
and starts to really fight...
Priscilla doesn't
stand a chance.
After all, she is
our top ranked warrior...
What's going on...?
I'm getting so much slower...
And she's getting faster...!
But why?
Why is this
happening to me...?
She's the villain here...
I've always worked
so hard to save humans,
and she's killed
so many of them.
So why can't I win...?
Why can't I defeat her...?
It isn't fair!
No warrior has ever possessed
such incredible raw ability...
There is no telling how
powerful she could become.
And even if we
both walk away from this...
who can say what
will happen the next time?
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but I don't think I'm ready
to die just yet.
Damn.
Nice cut...
It looks good...
I've never had one.
Yep, you'll have to tell me
all about what it's like
to be kicked such
a great distance.
We can't...
It's wrong...
It's too cruel to make her
fight all four of us together.
We don't even
fight Yoma like this...
Let me finish her.
Don't be so naïve!
If it weren't for
our assistance,
your head would no longer
be attached to your body...
don't let your misguided sense
of honor cloud your judgment.
Teresa is no longer a warrior.
She is a criminal who has
betrayed the Organization...
she doesn't deserve your honor.
Now - we've been sent here
to end her existence.
And that's exactly what
we are going to do...
Priscilla, I want you to
focus all of your power
into taking the life
of that murderer...
Now go!
I understand...
I will bring her down...
Traitors must be
stopped at all costs!
My apologies, Teresa...
If I had my choice,
I alone would destroy you...
But you have brought this on-
Yourself!
Terror raises
it's head to cry...
And terror raises the curtain
on a horrible tragedy.
Next time, Awakening.