You're so slow...
I really didn't
expect much, but this?
There are so many unnecessary
movements in your attacks.
Same with your
defensive maneuvers...
I could teach you to move
so much more efficiently.
But I believe
we've passed that point.
I apologize.
I'm still worked
up from fighting
such a strong adversary...
But killing you should
help me wind down.
Damned Awakened Beings...
I'll never rest until I've torn
every single one of you apart.
Just what do you
think you're doing?
You've picked
an interesting time
to suppress your Yoma power...
Have you given up already?
And I came all this way...
Oh, well.
My, you are full of surprises!
Are you reading my Yoki aura
to anticipate my attacks?
That is a fancy little trick.
Maybe this won't be
as boring as I thought.
You saw it coming.
You are perceptive.
And right when I was
going to show you
the new move
I've been working on.
What was that...?
I've never felt
anything like it before.
Do me a favor...
And try not to die after
the first blow, all right?
She's swinging at
my right shoulder from below.
And my left shoulder,
from above!
How...?
I can see the path
of her sword...
Why can't I defend against it?
Impossible...!
Her sword moved...
like a snake!
It's a shame, really.
In combat with
any other opponent,
I bet you would do pretty well.
But against me you're
doomed from the start.
Do you know something, Clare...?
Unlike the rest of you,
I have never been honored
with a, cute,
little nickname...
You know the ones I'm
talking about, don't you,
names like 'Phantom Miria',
or 'Quick Sword Ilena'?
So for years I worked tirelessly
to create the technique
you just witnessed.
I call it the
'Rippling Sword'...
Like it?
Her sword!
Her arm is vibrating
so quickly it looks
like the blade is alive.
It's not a bad trick is it...?
I was thinking something
like 'Rippling Ophelia'...
Tell me the truth, now.
Is it catchy enough?
The only problem is that
I can't get the word out
about my new name.
Because nobody
that's seen it...
Has ever lived
to tell anyone else.
Damn it!
I can't stop that attack even if
I can anticipate her moves.
My god...
You just don't know
when to give up, do you...?
Any chance that you may have
had at winning is long gone.
A chance at winning...?
I never had any such thing...
Not against that!
What...?
A head-on attack, huh?
Such a disappointment.
You look like you're
in pain, Clare.
I'd be happy to end it.
And I had been told
that you had potential...
I guess everyone makes mistakes.
Damn...
I let myself get cut too deeply.
Oh well.
There's nothing I could do...
Any shallower and she would
have suspected something...
I'm going to have to
move quickly if I want
to get my arm reattached.
That was quite a display.
And you actually came pretty
close to getting away with it.
Letting me cut off your arm
was an excellent touch.
My last blow even felt
like it was deep enough
to finish you off...
Did you plan to lead me to that
cliff for your little show?
Surely you hadn't been stringing
me along the whole time.
No, that would just be too...
impressive.
But it would have been
more convincing if you'd
given up on that arm of yours.
You never once let go of it...
And that's what gave you away.
Did you know?
There are offensive fighters...
And those who excel
in tactical defense...
Obviously you belong
in the first category...
An attacker...
Don't you agree?
Unfortunately for you,
Attackers are notoriously
bad at healing...
They can reattach severed limbs,
but they'll never be able
to regenerate a part of the body
if it's been lost or destroyed.
So when you chose to live
the life of a half-human,
half-monster, were you
thinking about revenge,
or more concerned
with your own survival?
That does tend to be the
deciding factor in producing
an Attacker or a Defender...
Which was it for you?
Well...
Either way, it'd be silly
to let you keep that arm.
You don't really think
I'll let you reattach it...?
Because you'd be
very wrong indeed.
Oh, too bad...
Letting me cut off your dominant
arm wasn't the greatest idea.
Struggling is pointless...
I think you'll realize it,
too- if you think about it.
Hey.
I won't think less
of you if you give up...
I didn't think much
of you to begin with...
Honestly, you're barely more
of a challenge than that boy
you were traveling with.
Alright, why don't you try
to pick up your sword now.
Why are you trying
to stay alive, anyway...?
That one last thing
to do before you die,
or some sort of
survival instinct...?
Really, why won't you
just accept your fate?
Look at me asking like I care.
I was lured here by the presence
of something familiar...
But both of you
are strangers to me.
Who the hell are you?
Well, no matter.
You'll soon find I don't
tolerate interruption...
For your rudeness,
you'll die anyway!
Get away!
She's dangerous...!
Run!
I see...
It's you.
How the...
How the hell did
you just do that?!
Tell me!
Looks like things
are different now...
Claymores will turn
their swords on anyone.
What's wrong...?
I can't even touch her!
I don't get it.
Get back!
Quick...!
Her sword--
Your swordsmanship
has potential...
I imagine your ranking must
be in the single digits.
But numbers and symbols don't
matter out here I'm afraid...
What...
is this...?
Her blade is moving
too fast to see.
It can't be her...!
How is she alive?
She was one of the
enforcers sent to kill Teresa!
The former Number Two!
Quick Sword Ilena!
Why are you trying
to stay alive, anyway...?
That one last thing
to do before you die,
or some sort of
survival instinct...?
Really.
Why won't you
just accept your fate?
Where am I?
What's going on?
Your injuries were
substantial and reattaching
your hand was difficult...
I'm sorry but there was no way
you could have regenerated
your other arm
in your condition.
You're Ilena!
Where did you bring me...?
I don't understand...
Why are you doing all this?
No more questions until
you've eaten something...
You've had no food
or water for seven days.
It must be starting
to take its toll.
It's been seven days...?
What the hell
have you done with my sword?
Sit.
I have to get--
If your life really
means that little to you...
I wish I'd never gone
to the trouble of saving you.
Now listen to me carefully,
the Claymore who was chasing you
is still alive.
She's hurt worse than you
were when I found you,
but she is not dead.
Then there's your arm.
Are you listening...?
Your weaker hand has become
your only hand, and if you
want to defend yourself you
must study how to use it.
As you are now, I doubt that
you could even slay a human.
You cannot change things...
So accept them.
Dammit!
Dammit...!
That little girl
is all grown up.
Did you finish your food?
Yes...
I really had no idea how hungry
I was until I started eating.
Everything was wonderful...
I appreciate it.
You knew my name
as soon as you saw me...
What else do you know?
I know everything...
everything that had
to do with Teresa.
And that would include
Priscilla, am I right?
Yes.
In your time...
a young Priscilla rose
quickly to Number Two.
But she drew too deeply
on her Yoki and awakened
during the mission...
She killed Teresa,
as well as the other enforcers,
and vanished.
I never thought that
Priscilla might have left
any one of you alive.
I was surprised, as well.
Who would have guessed
that scared little girl
would become a warrior?
Whose blood do you
have inside you...?
Teresa's?
You were lucky
to escape with your life...
It was your last chance
to live as a human,
to forget about all of this...
Now you're looking
for Pricilla, aren't you?
Thank you for caring for me...
Now give me my sword,
and I'll be going.
Forget about vengeance, girl...
Priscilla is more powerful
than any opponent
you have ever encountered...
No living warrior could
ever hope to challenge her.
You're at a greater disadvantage
than those who are half-Yoma...
If you do have Teresa's blood...
You're a quarter...
You are inferior
to her in every way.
If you're finished,
I would like my sword back.
Look at me.
I was a higher rank than you
the time that I tried to defeat
Priscilla and look
what she left me with.
In that fight...
I realized no matter
how we struggled,
Priscilla had awakened
with such power we could
never bring her down.
I ran.
I let everyone
believe I was dead,
and chose a home far from
the Organization...
I have lived here, suppressing
my Yoki aura, ever since.
I've hidden it for so
many years I doubt any
of our comrades
could detect it now.
You've given up fighting?
Why?
Your swordsmanship
is still superb,
even if you do
only have one arm.
I suppose...
I'm afraid.
I have never escaped
the terror I felt that day...
You were there-
you should know.
I was there...
I do know.
Wait.
What is driving you?
Teresa is a part of me...
And not just the
blood flowing in my veins.
I once lost a family,
my ability to speak...
Even the will to live...
Teresa gave those
things back to me.
Everything I've ever
known came from Teresa,
and what she sacrificed.
She gave her life so that I
could have the opportunity
to live a normal,
human existence.
But I wasn't strong enough- I
couldn't just forget everything
that had happened that day
and live the life Teresa
wanted for me to live.
I understand...
And I offer you my help.
If you must go after Priscilla,
your willingness to fight her
is the only thing that will
qualify you to do so.
Now...
You face a
difficult decision...
Seek your revenge or survive.
Forgive me, but I don't believe
I ever asked you your name.
My name is Clare.
Very well, then, Clare.
Your instruction in the Quick
Sword will begin in the morning.
It hurts...
Oh god...
Brother, where are you?
Help me, brother...!
Please, I need you...!
You said you'd protect me.
Well, I need you
here with me now!
Where are you...?
Why did you leave me?
You promised.
You promised me.
That bitch!
She won't get away with this!
Brother?
What brother?
Who the hell am I
talking about?
Like I care about some weakling
human who let himself
get killed with
a fucking smile on his face!
Like I give a damn about that
lousy, worthless son of a bitch!
Fuck you...
Fuck you!
That's enough for today.
Stop.
The key to mastering the
Quick-Sword is isolating
your Yoma power
in just one arm...
You must allow your entire
arm to become awakened.
It requires nothing
less than an iron will.
And it will take
a strong mind...
The amount of concentration
needed to control
an awakened arm is tremendous.
Is that so?
Then how come you
haven't broken a sweat
the whole time
we've been training?
So are you giving up...?
Have you had all you can take?
Not a chance.
We just started...
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Then get back on your feet...
Only in battle can you discover
your limits, and you must learn
how much power to
release into your arm.
How interesting.
I can't put my finger on it...
But I feel better than
I have in a long time...
I can barely even remember
why I was so upset...
And I'm hungry...
Odd...
I'm never hungry...
But somehow...
I'm in the mood for innards.
It was proof...
Proof that once,
she had been alive...
A testament to her existence.
Next time...
"To Be Qualified to Fight."