♪
( singing in Japanese )
( JoJo gasps )
ALL THE AIR, IT SEEMS TO BE
FLOWING OVER TO WAMUU.
Wamuu: MY ULTIMATE MASTERY,
ATMOSPHERIC RIFT!
( JoJo gasps )
THAT'S ONLY WIND?
Wamuu: I KNOW
YOU'RE NEAR THE FLAME.
I SENSE IT, THOUGH I CAN'T SEE
EXACTLY WHERE THAT IS,
BUT I AM GOING
TO FIND YOU EVENTUALLY.
NOW THAT I'VE PREVENTED YOU
FROM GATHERING
YOUR HAMON ENERGY,
I'M GOING TO CUT YOU IN HALF.
Kars: ATMOSPHERIC RIFT
IS WAMUU'S
SUPREME FINAL WEAPON.
THE PIPES
HE USES TO CLOAK HIMSELF
TAKE IN HUGE AMOUNTS OF AIR
AND THEN
UNBELIEVABLY COMPRESS IT.
THE AIR IS THEN BLASTED FROM
AN ORIFICE THINNER THAN PAPER.
IT IS A RAZOR MADE OF WIND.
BUT IT CREATES HEAT AND FRICTION
AT LEVELS
TERRIBLE EVEN FOR WAMUU.
HIS BODY CANNOT HANDLE IT.
HE IS FALLING APART.
BUT HE IS CERTAINLY
A BREATHTAKING FIGURE,
TRAGIC AND HEROIC.
VICTORY IS YOURS, WAMUU!
TAKE HIS LIFE
AS A BALM FOR YOUR WOUNDS.
Lisa Lisa: JOJO!
JoJo: IT'S GETTING CLOSE.
TIME TO PULL OFF
ONE OF MY FAMOUS TRICKS NOW.
THIS ONE'S CALLED
THE HAMON OIL TRICK.
HIS LUNGS ARE LITERALLY
HIGH‐PRESSURE OXYGEN TANKS.
THOSE PIPES,
IF I CAN ONLY HIT THEM,
HE'D INHALE THE FLAMING OIL,
WHICH IN TURN WOULD CREATE
AN INTERNAL EXPLOSION.
BUT THIS IS
THE VERY LAST ACE UP MY SLEEVE.
IF I MESS IT UP‐‐
( screams )
Wamuu: GOT YOU NOW.
YOUR LIFE IS MINE.
JoJo: DAMN IT!
TAKE THIS, WAMUU!
Wamuu: HMM?
THAT'S YOUR CHOICE?
FOOL. I CAN SENSE ANYTHING
THAT IS FAR ENOUGH AWAY
FROM THE FIRE.
YOU'RE OUT OF TRICKS,
AND THAT CRY OF YOURS
GAVE AWAY YOUR POSITION.
( JoJo grunts )
Wamuu: AND NOW...
ATMOSPHERIC RIFT!
JoJo: CAESAR!
LEND ME YOUR STRENGTH!
Wamuu: ANOTHER FIRE ATTACK?
I TOLD YOU
I CAN SENSE THESE THINGS.
AND NOW I WILL CUT YOU IN HALF
TO CLAIM MY VICTORY.
Lisa Lisa: JOJO, NO!
Kars: NOW HE HAS FINALLY WON.
JoJo: WAMUU...
( man singing opera )
LET ME TELL YOU
EXACTLY WHEN YOU LOST.
IT WAS WHEN I THREW
CAESAR'S SCARF.
Wamuu: EH?
JoJo: DON'T YOU GET IT?
I MEANT FOR YOU
TO CUT THE BOTTLE IN HALF
THE ENTIRE TIME.
YOUR ABILITY TO DO IT
SO QUICKLY AND EASILY
IS WHAT LED TO YOUR DOWNFALL.
( Wamuu gasps )
THE OIL INSIDE OF IT
IS NOW VAPORIZING.
AND LOOK. YOU SEE THE BANDANA,
ALL THE PIECES FLYING AROUND?
Wamuu: EVERY LITTLE FRAGMENT
IS STILL ON FIRE,
AND THEY'RE ENTERING MY BODY.
( opera singing continues )
JoJo: WAMUU, YOU HAVE BEEN
A WORTHY AND ADMIRABLE FIGHTER,
BUT A POWERFUL ALLY NAMED CAESAR
WAS WITH ME
THROUGHOUT THIS CONTEST.
( Wamuu groans )
♪
Vampire: HE WAS DEFEATED.
Vampire #2: LORD WAMUU.
HOW COULD HE HAVE LOST?
( Kars grunts )
( Wamuu grunting )
( JoJo breathing deeply )
Lisa Lisa: JOJO, BE CAREFUL.
HE CAN REGENERATE,
EVEN LIKE THAT,
AFTER BEING BLOWN TO BITS.
YOU HAVE TO USE
YOUR STRONGEST HAMON
TO DESTROY HIM COMPLETELY.
♪
Wamuu: SO IT IS
FINALLY OVER NOW, JOJO.
JoJo: IT IS.
Wamuu: YOU TOOK REVENGE
FOR CAESAR.
JoJo: YES, I DID.
Wamuu: THEN GO AHEAD.
FINISH IT.
JoJo: I WILL!
( boom )
( Wamuu groans )
♪
( groans ) WHAT IS GOING ON?
JoJo: THAT SMOKE
ISN'T FROM THE FLAMING OIL.
IT'S COMING FROM YOUR WOUNDS.
THE HAMON FROM YOUR ARMS
SPREAD THROUGH YOU.
EVERY PART OF YOU
IS INFECTED NOW.
YOU ARE DISSOLVING.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE
THE AGONY YOU FEEL.
I CAN'T PREVENT YOU
FROM DYING NOW,
BUT THERE'S THIS.
MY BLOOD CAN
AT LEAST EASE YOUR PAIN.
Wamuu: WHY DO YOU
WANT TO SHAME ME?
I HAVE MADE PEACE WITH MYSELF.
STOP. I DON'T NEED
PITY FROM YOU.
JoJo: IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK?
THAT THIS IS DONE
OUT OF PITY FOR YOU? NO.
WHY DIDN'T YOU DESTROY
CAESAR'S BUBBLE OF BLOOD
THAT CARRIED
HIS BANDANA AND RING,
KNOWING FULL WELL THAT THEY
POSED A SERIOUS THREAT TO YOU?
WAS THAT PITY?
Wamuu: IT WAS BECAUSE THE MAN
WAS A WORTHY AND NOBLE WARRIOR.
HE DESERVED
TO BE HONORED FOR THAT.
JoJo: WHAT YOU'LL SAY NEXT IS,
"JOJO, YOU CAN'T MEAN..."
Wamuu: JOJO, YOU CAN'T MEAN...
JoJo: YES, I DO, WAMUU.
THE HONOR YOU SHOWED MY FRIEND,
CAESAR'S WARRIOR SPIRIT,
HAD EARNED YOUR RESPECT.
SO IN RETURN,
I WANTED TO FIND A WAY
TO HONOR YOUR WARRIOR SPIRIT.
MY BLOOD IS A TRIBUTE TO YOU.
( Wamuu chuckles )
YOU BEAT ME, JOJO.
AND AS A WARRIOR,
IT WOULD NOW APPEAR
THAT YOU STAND TALLER THAN I DO.
♪
Vampire #3: KILL THE BASTARD!
( vampires yell )
Wamuu: HOLD!
WHAT BETRAYAL IS THIS?
‐ ( vampires growl )
‐ JoJo: HUH?
Wamuu: YOU COWARDLY ANIMALS!
( vampire #5 screams )
JoJo: WAMUU!
WHY DO THAT?
Wamuu: I AM WAMUU.
ALTHOUGH SWORN TO LORD KARS,
I WILL NOT ALLOW
THE VAMPIRES TO ATTACK YOU.
IT'S NOT BECAUSE OF SENTIMENT.
I TOLD CAESAR THIS AS WELL.
TO ME,
ONLY THE STRONG TRULY EXISTED.
VICTORY WAS THE SINGLE QUALITY
TO BE ADMIRED.
I EXISTED ONLY ACCORDING
TO MY OWN CODE OF HONOR.
JOJO, PLEASE UNDERSTAND,
TO ME, IMMORTALITY
WAS SOMETHING UTTERLY
UNIMPORTANT AND TRIVIAL.
ALL THAT HAS EVER MATTERED TO ME
WAS LIVING UP TO MY CODE.
( JoJo sighs )
Wamuu: AND NOW...
I DESIRE THAT YOU
SHOULD DRINK THE ANTIDOTE.
YOU MUST DO IT BEFORE I
DISSOLVE COMPLETELY AWAY.
JoJo: YOU WON'T SEE IT, THOUGH.
Wamuu: I DON'T NEED EYES,
WORDS, OR A HORN.
I WILL KNOW IT.
WHAT MATTERS IS THAT YOU DO IT.
( JoJo swallows )
Wamuu: I HAVE NO REGRETS.
I AM GLAD I WAS ABLE TO WITNESS
YOUR GROWTH AS A WARRIOR.
PERHAPS THE REASON I LIVED
THESE THOUSANDS OF YEARS
WAS SO THAT I COULD MEET YOU
AT THE END.
( wind blowing )
FAREWELL TO YOU,
WARRIOR JOJO.
♪
Narrator: WAMUU BECAME
ONE WITH THE WIND.
JOJO GAVE HIS OPPONENT
ONE FINAL SALUTE.
THOUGH NO TEARS FELL,
THEY HAD SHARED A SILENT SONG.
THEY HAD SHARED
A WARRIOR'S AFFINITY.
Kars: WAMUU...
YOU MUST KILL HIM.
Wamuu: BUT, MY LORD KARS,
WITH UTMOST RESPECT, HE IS
ONLY AN INNOCENT YOUNG BOY.
Kars: THAT'S TRUE, JUST A BOY.
THAT IS THE REASON HE MUST DIE.
IF THESE HAMON USERS
ARE ALLOWED TO LIVE,
THEY'RE LIKELY TO BECOME
OUR MORTAL ENEMIES,
AND HUMANS GROW
VERY QUICKLY INDEED.
Wamuu: HMM.
Kars: IS IT BEYOND YOU?
IT WOULD SEEM I MUST DEMONSTRATE
HOW IT IS DONE.
NOW, RESOLVING THE PROBLEM
IS HANDLED LIKE THIS, WAMUU!
WAMUU, HE WAS TOO PURE
IN HIS WARRIOR PHILOSOPHY,
AND HE BECAME WEAK AS A RESULT.
Vampire #6:
WELL, THAT'S THE END OF WAMUU.
Vampire #7: INDEED IT IS.
WHAT A DISAPPOINTMENT.
Vampire #8: YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE'S ONLY A POSER.
Lisa Lisa: YOUR FOLLOWERS
ARE SUCH BASE CREATURES.
MAKES ME WANT TO VOMIT.
( vampires gasp, gag )
‐ ( groaning )
‐ Vampire #6: NO, DON'T.
LORD KARS, WE‐‐
Vampire #7:
HE'S DRAINING US DRY.
Kars: I ALONE
AM THE ONLY ONE TO REMAIN...
BECAUSE...
THIS WORLD AND ALL IN IT
BELONG TO ME.
‐ ( vampires gasping )
‐ Vampire #9: LOOK AT HIM! LOOK!
LORD KARS IS AMAZING!
Vampire #10: OUR LORD
IS READY TO FIGHT!
Vampire #11: LISTEN, LORD KARS,
THERE'S NO REASON FOR YOU
TO WASTE TIME
ON ANY ONE‐ON‐ONE BATTLES.
Vampire #12: FORGET THE RULES.
LET US KILL THESE TWO FOR YOU.
Vampire #13: FOR YOU, LORD,
WE'LL TURN THEM
INTO SPRAYS OF BLOOD!
JoJo: JUST WHAT
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD DO.
( vampires gasp )
Lisa Lisa: I TOLD YOU.
Vampire #14:
THE RED STONE! LOOK!
Lisa Lisa: IT'S ME
AGAINST KARS ONE‐ON‐ONE,
BUT IF THOSE TERMS
AREN'T TO YOUR LIKING,
WHY DON'T I JUST SMASH
THIS THING RIGHT HERE AND NOW?
Kars: I WILL HONOR MY WORD.
A ONE‐ON‐ONE FIGHT, COUNT ON IT.
MY PROMISE STANDS.
THAT IS WHY I CHOSE
TO REVEAL MY HORN TO YOU.
AS FOR MY UNDERLINGS' BEHAVIOR,
AS YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE,
THEY ARE ALREADY DEAD.
( vampires gasp )
Vampire #14: WHY, LORD KARS?
( bodies thud )
Kars: ALL I WANT
IS THAT RED STONE.
HOWEVER, THOUGH,
ESIDISI AND WAMUU
WERE MY COMRADES
FOR 10,000 YEARS.
I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO HONOR
BOTH THEIR WARRIOR DEATHS
AND THEIR WARRIOR PRIDE.
I WILL FIGHT
YOU HAMON USERS FAIRLY,
AND THEN I WILL FINISH THIS
WITH MY OWN TWO HANDS.
FOR YOU, LISA LISA,
SEEING THE FIGHTER YOU ARE,
I WILL NOT THINK OF YOU
AS MERELY A WOMAN.
I WILL FIGHT YOU
WITH ALL THE STRENGTH
I HAVE AT MY COMMAND.
COME WITH ME.
THAT IS WHERE WE SHALL FIGHT...
THE TEMPLE AT PIZ BERNINA.
CHAMPIONS OF BATTLE
WOULD COME HERE TO DRINK
THE BLOOD OF THOSE THEY
HAD FELLED MIXED WITH LIQUOR.
THEY THANKED THE GODS
FOR THE GIFT OF LIFE.
IT'S NOT AN ARENA, BUT IT
WILL SERVE FOR OUR FIGHT.
JoJo: COACH LISA LISA,
YOU MAY BE EXTREMELY SKILLED,
BUT YOU ARE STILL A WOMAN.
HE DOESN'T LOOK
AS STRONG AS WAMUU WAS.
LET ME TAKE HIM FOR YOU.
Lisa Lisa: I WILL NOT.
♪
I DIDN'T LIVE MY LIFE AS I DID
AND TRAIN ALL THOSE YEARS
TO BE REPLACED
BY SOME STRIPLING.
JoJo: OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVE LIVED A LOT OF YEARS.
Kars: I SHALL USE
MY BRILLIANT BONE BLADES.
IT WOULD OFFEND WAMUU'S MEMORY
IF I DIDN'T OFFER YOU
THE WEAPON OF YOUR CHOICE.
FEEL FREE TO PICK
ANYTHING YOU LIKE.
Lisa Lisa: MY SCARF
WILL BE MORE THAN SUFFICIENT.
Kars: AS YOU WILL.
AND NOW LET'S FIGHT.
♪
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
REMARKABLE. THERE IS
NO VIOLENCE IN HIS STANCE.
HOW CAN HE FIGHT
WITHOUT VIOLENCE?
Kars: WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU NOT READY?
APPARENTLY
THE FIRST MOVE IS MINE!
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
JoJo: HE DISAPPEARED COMPLETELY
IN THAT SUDDEN WHITE LIGHT.
WHERE'D HE GO?
Lisa Lisa: KARS IS HERE.
I‐I CAN FEEL HIM.
BUT HE SEEMS TO BE COMING
FROM ABOVE AS WELL AS BELOW.
( wind blowing )
♪
Kars: ATTACK
OF THE BRILLIANT BONE BLADE!
LOOK! IN THE PILLAR,
THERE'S A CRACK!
Lisa Lisa: SNAKE MUFFLER.
Kars: EH?
Lisa Lisa: WHAT YOU DON'T KNOW
IS THIS SATIPOROJA BEETLE SCARF
IS ABLE TO CONDUCT
HAMON ENERGY PERFECTLY.
IT'S BOTH A DEADLY WEAPON
AND A LIFE DETECTOR,
AND IT PROTECTS AGAINST
BEING ATTACKED FROM BEHIND!
( Kars screaming )
JoJo: ALL RIGHT. A KNOCKOUT.
MY WONDERFUL COACH
REALLY GOT HIM GOOD.
HE DIDN'T REALLY
COMPARE TO WAMUU,
BUT DOGS WHO BARK RARELY BITE.
COACH, I HAVE TO SAY THAT YOU
REALLY ARE BETTER THAN ME.
‐ ( blade slices )
‐ ( Lisa Lisa gasps )
( JoJo gasps )
♪
Vampire #15: HELP ME.
HELP ME, LORD KARS.
( JoJo gasps )
KARS IS BEHIND HER.
THEN WHO'S THAT?
WHO'S AT HER FEET?
IT CAN'T BE.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?!
KARS WASN'T THE ONE FIGHTING
WITH HER. HE USED A DOUBLE!
( Lisa Lisa gags )
( Kars scoffs )
WHAT STUPIDITY.
WHY WOULD I EVER CHOOSE
TO FIGHT ONE‐ON‐ONE?
THE ONLY THING I WANTED
OUT OF THIS WAS THE RED STONE,
BECAUSE I PLAN TO BECOME
THE ULTIMATE LIFE‐FORM.
I AM NOT A WARRIOR‐PHILOSOPHER
LIKE WAMUU WAS,
NOR AM I A ROMANTIC.
NO MATTER THE METHOD UTILIZED,
IN THE END...
VICTORY IS THE ONLY THING
THAT MATTERS!
( JoJo screams )
Lisa Lisa: SO THAT'S WHY
I SENSED NO VIOLENCE.
HE NEVER HAD ANY INTENTION
OF FIGHTING ME.
Kars: IT'S OVER!
Lisa Lisa: JO...JO.
Kars: I HAVE THE RED STONE.
THE ONLY THING THAT'S LEFT
IS FOR ALL OF YOU TO MAKE ME
HAPPY BY KILLING JOJO!
( JoJo roars )
KARS. KARS!
YOU ARE GOING TO PAY!
( vampires yell )
JoJo: KARS!
OUT OF THE WAY! MOVE BACK!
I'LL SPLIT YOUR DAMNED SKULLS
AND KILL YOU!
ZOOM PUNCH!
Vampire #16: EH?
( chuckles )
( JoJo gasps )
Vampire #16: YOUR HAMON,
I DON'T THINK
IT'S WORKING ANYMORE.
YOU'RE WEAK NOW, SO WE'RE‐‐
JoJo: REBUFF OVERDRIVE!
( panting )
Kars: JOJO, YOU LOOK
COMPLETELY WORN OUT.
YOUR BREATHING IS RAGGED,
YOUR HAMON LEVEL IS WEAK,
AND YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE LEFT
OUT OF ALL OF THE HAMON USERS
THAT LISA LISA TRAINED.
CAN YOU LAST?
WILL YOU LAST?
JOJO...
THINK YOU CAN BEAT ME?
( chuckles ) MMM.
( vampire #17 chuckles )
JoJo: WHAT? IT CAN'T BE GONE.
Vampire #17:
LET'S RIP OFF HIS SKIN!
JoJo: AH, CRAP. YOU CAN TRY!
Vampire #17: EH? ( gags )
( vampires groan )
Kars: EH?
JoJo: TH‐THAT LIGHT.
♪
AND THAT FACE.
Von Stroheim:
THIS IS YOUR WARNING, VAMPIRES.
YOU ARE NOW FACING
MAJOR VON STROHEIM
UND THE GERMAN ELITE.
Men: AND WE REPRESENT
THE SPECIAL FORCES
OF THE SPEEDWAGON FOUNDATION!
‐ Speedwagon: JOJO.
‐ Smokey: JOJO.
JoJo: DAMN.
SPEEDWAGON, YOU LOOK GREAT.
AND, SMOKEY, TOO.
YOU'RE A SIGHT FOR SORE EYES.
( Smokey laughs )
( Von Stroheim chuckles )
MY RIGHT LEG
MIGHT BE STIFF NOW,
BUT MY BODY IS BETTER
THAN IT EVER WAS BEFORE.
NOW ALL YOU VAMPIRES WILL SEE
WHAT GERMAN SCIENCE CAN DO!
TASTE OUR
ULTRAVIOLET FLOODLIGHTS!
( vampires scream )
Speedwagon: IT WAS
THE SPEEDWAGON FOUNDATION
THAT MADE THEM
SMALL ENOUGH TO CARRY,
BUT OUR BOY DOES LIKE TO BRAG.
( men yell )
( vampires screaming )
Kars: HMM.
CRAFTY CREATURES, NO QUESTION.
HMM?
I DON'T SEE JOJO DOWN THERE.
( sighs ) GONE AGAIN.
EH?
OH, YOU'RE JUST AS QUICK
AS EVER, AREN'T YOU?
TAKE EYES OFF YOU FOR A SECOND,
AND THERE YOU ARE PUTTING
ANOTHER LITTLE SCHEME IN PLAY.
JoJo: YOU CROSSED A LINE.
NO HONOR EARNS YOU
NO CONSIDERATION.
YOU SAID IT WOULD BE
A FAIR FIGHT,
BUT ATTACKED LISA LISA
IN A COWARDLY AMBUSH,
THEREBY SHOWING
WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF.
AND YOU HAVE BETRAYED
THE HONOR AND MEMORY
OF YOUR FRIEND WAMUU.
Kars: SAVE YOUR INDIGNATION.
YOUR OUTRAGE MEANS NOTHING.
ANY ACTION IS A MEANS TO AN END
FOR WHAT I DESIRE.
THE THING THAT MATTERS TO ME
IS THE RED STONE.
BATTLING OVER THOUSANDS OF YEARS
MEANS MINIMIZING DANGER,
NOT TAKING ANY RISK,
AND MOVING YOUR PAWNS
VERY CAREFULLY INDEED.
THIS IS WHAT THE BATTLE
HAS BEEN ABOUT.
AND TO SHOW YOU
HOW GOOD I AM AT THIS,
I'M GOING TO MANEUVER YOU
EFFORTLESSLY TO YOUR DEATH.
JoJo: LISTEN TO ME.
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, KARS,
I'VE NEVER HATED ANYONE
BEFORE THIS DAY,
BUT YOU, I HATE!
Kars: YOU REALLY HATE ME?
THEN SHOW ME, JOJO.
LET'S GO ONE‐ON‐ONE.
WE'LL HAVE THAT FAIR FIGHT
YOU WANTED TO HAVE.
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( Kars chuckles )
LISA LISA IS ALMOST DEAD,
BUT NOT COMPLETELY YET.
I LEFT HER ALIVE.
MY PLAN IS TO LET HER LIVE
FOR A WHILE.
AND WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
SHE'S JUST ANOTHER PAWN,
A WORTHLESS LITTLE PAWN
I CAN USE AGAINST YOU.
( imitates electric guitar )
( laughs )
( imitating electric guitar )
JoJo: YOU UTTER BASTARD.
Kars: HAH!
NOW I'VE TIED HER FEET TOGETHER
WITH THIS ROPE.
AND DO YOU KNOW WHY?
WHY WOULD I DO
SUCH A THING AS THIS?
THIS IS WHY!
JoJo: LISA LISA, NO!
Kars: OFF YOU GO.
IF SHE HITS THE GROUND,
SHE'LL BE DEAD.
IF YOU DON'T SAVE HER
IN A FEW SECONDS,
SHE'LL BE
A LISA‐LISA‐SHAPED SPLATTER.
( laughs )
Von Stroheim: HUH?
Speedwagon: WHAT?! JOJO!
LISA LISA!
Smokey: HMM? LISA LISA?
THAT LISA LISA?
DO YOU MEAN TO SAY
SHE'S THE BABY
ON THE SHIP
GRANNY ERINA TOLD US ABOUT?
♪
THEN THAT MEANS
SHE IS JOJO'S...
Kars: NOW THAT YOU
CAN'T MOVE FROM THAT SPOT,
HERE'S HOW EFFICIENT
BATTLE CAN BE, JOJO.
I'LL VERY CALMLY
WALK RIGHT UP TO YOU
AND SLICE YOU TO PIECES
WHILE YOU CAN'T MOVE!
( JoJo yells )
KARS, YOU BASTARD!
THERE'S A PLACE
WAITING FOR YOU IN HELL!
Smokey: JOJO DOESN'T KNOW.
HE DOESN'T KNOW THE WOMAN
HE'S TRYING TO SAVE
IS HIS MOTHER.
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Speedwagon: HAVE YOU FINISHED
DISPOSING OF THOSE VAMPIRES YET?
Kars: I'M TAKING YOUR LIFE
AT THE MOMENT OF MY CHOICE.
‐ JoJo: THE SCARF IS A GAMBLE.
‐ Erina: POOR LITTLE CHILD.
Speedwagon: VON STROHEIM,
YOU MUST STOP!
Von Stroheim: THIS CAN'T BE!