♪
Von Stroheim: JOJO...
I'VE HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT YOU.
( groans )
LISTEN, AND LISTEN GOOD.
SANTVIENTO HERE,
THE SO‐CALLED PILLAR MAN,
USES A MASK TO TURN MEN
INTO VAMPIRES.
HE DOES THIS
TO MAKE THEM STRONGER,
UND THEN HE DEVOURS THEM.
DESTROY HIM! TAKE HIM OUT
WHILE THERE'S STILL TIME!
Speedwagon: DON'T DO IT, JOJO!
HE'S DANGEROUS!
JoJo: YOU'RE IT.
( laughs )
OH, I GET IT.
YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE
STRONG, SILENT TYPES, RIGHT?
EVER THOUGHT ABOUT MODELING?
YOU'VE GOT A NICE LOOK THERE.
COME ON. LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
GIVE ME A SMILE.
‐ ( both gasp )
‐ JoJo: I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
SHOW ME SOME VULNERABILITY.
WORK WITH ME HERE.
MAKE SOME LOVE TO THE CAMERA.
READY? SET?
GIVE ME HAPPY. NOW BE SILLY.
SHOW US THOSE PEARLY WHITES.
HEH.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
JoJo: COME ON, BIG GUY.
SMILE AT THE BIRDIE.
Von Stroheim: JOJO,
STOP THIS NONSENSE IMMEDIATELY!
Speedwagon: DON'T PROVOKE HIM.
PLEASE, JOJO,
SANTVIENTO IS DANGEROUS.
JoJo: YEAH, I KNOW
YOU THINK HE'S DANGEROUS,
BUT I HAVE A THEORY
THAT MAYBE HE'S NOT SO BAD.
LET ME TEST SOMETHING OUT HERE.
I DON'T WANT TO ASSUME HE'S EVIL
JUST BECAUSE HE KILLED
A BUNCH OF BRAINLESS‐‐
Von Stroheim:
WHAT ARE YOU, INSANE?!
IF HE'S NOT EVIL,
WHY DID HE KILL ALL MY MEN?!
JoJo: DON'T KNOW. SOME WOULD SAY
YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHAT'S HAPPENED.
WEREN'T YOU THE ONE
EXPERIMENTING ON HIM
AND TRYING TO BLAST HIM AWAY
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
NOT THAT I
REALLY CARE ABOUT THAT.
THE ONLY REASON I'M HERE
TO MAKE SURE THAT SPEEDWAGON
MAKES IT BACK TO NEW YORK
SAFE AND SOUND.
ANYWAY, I'M NOT HERE TO FIGHT,
AND I'M FEELING GENEROUS.
COME ON. LOOSEN UP, BIG GUY.
HOW 'BOUT THAT SMILE?
( gasps )
♪
THAT WAS RUDE.
HE JUST WALKED THROUGH ME
LIKE I WASN'T EVEN THERE.
WHO THE HELL
DOES THIS GUY THINK HE IS?
MAYBE I SHOULD TEACH HIM
A QUICK LESSON.
HAVE A NICE TRIP.
WH‐WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
THAT WAS THE WEIRDEST FEELING,
AND IT HURT.
Santviento: WHAT IS THIS,
THIS TOOL?
COLD AND LONG...
WITH MANY DIFFERENT PIECES.
Speedwagon: HE DOES UNDERSTAND!
HE'S NOT SIMPLY MIMICKING.
IT TOOK HIM
PRACTICALLY NO TIME AT ALL
TO COMPLETELY MASTER
OUR LANGUAGE.
JoJo: HOW‐‐HOW IS HE DOING THAT?
HE TOOK IT APART.
HE DISMANTLED THAT ENTIRE WEAPON
LIKE SOME EXPERT GUNSMITH.
Von Stroheim: IT TAKES A SOLDIER
DOZENS OF HOURS
TO LEARN HOW TO FIELDSTRIP
HIS WEAPON THAT FAST.
Speedwagon: HE'S‐‐HE'S USING
HIS ADVANCED INTELLECT
TO LEARN EVERYTHING.
Santviento: SO BRIGHT.
THIS LIGHT IS NEW TO ME.
WHAT IS IT?
Speedwagon: DON'T YOU SEE?
WE WEREN'T THE ONES
OBSERVING ALL THIS TIME.
HE WAS ACTUALLY WATCHING US!
JoJo: HEY, BIG GUY,
YOU WANNA LEARN A NEW JOKE?
JUST STOP ME IF YOU'VE
HEARD THIS ONE BEFORE.
KNOCK, KNOCK. KNOCK, KNOCK.
‐ ( Von Stroheim gasps )
‐ Speedwagon: JOJO! GET AWAY!
Santviento: YOU ARE
PLAYING GAMES, PRIMITIVE.
I DO NOT WANT TO PLAY GAMES.
( JoJo gasps )
WHAT THE...
Narrator: RIB BLADES, SOMETIMES
KNOWN AS FIGHTING RIBS.
THEY ARE CAPABLE OF BEING
MANIPULATED IN ANY DIRECTION.
‐ Speedwagon: JOJO!
‐ ( JoJo grunting )
( gags )
( Santviento gasps )
SPARKS. ENERGY.
THIS HUMAN SEEMS...
DIFFERENT FROM THE OTHERS.
I WAS NOT ABLE TO ABSORB
HIS BODY INTO MINE.
HE JUST FLEW AWAY.
AND SOMEHOW HIS LEG,
IT REMAINS‐‐IT STILL SEEMS FINE.
THIS ONE IS SOMETHING NEW.
I HAVE YET TO SEE SUCH A HUMAN.
IS HE A UNIQUE SPECIMEN,
OR DO ALL HUMANS
OF HIS PARTICULAR CLASS
POSSESS THE SAME PROPERTIES?
COULD IT BE RELATED TO AGE?
( Speedwagon winces, screams )
Santviento: AH, NOW I SEE.
MY INSTINCT WAS RIGHT.
THAT HUMAN IS UNIQUE.
Speedwagon: AGH. JOJO, PLEASE.
MAKE IT STOP, PLEASE!
( Von Stroheim gasping )
JoJo: SPEEDWAGON.
THAT BASTARD.
LET THE OLD MAN GO, SANTVIENTO!
NOW I'M IN THE MOOD.
COME ON, BIG GUY.
YOU WANNA TRY AND TAKE ME ON?
Santviento: IT WOULD SEEM
THAT HUMANS HAVE EVOLVED
THEIR CONFIDENCE.
( JoJo yells )
HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY!
ONE HAMON SANDWICH COMING UP!
( grunts )
HUH? WHAT THE DEVIL?
MY HAMON
IS MAKING THAT BLOOD FLOAT.
SOMETHING'S WRONG HERE.
MY HAMON IS RUNNING OFF HIM
LIKE RAIN OFF A RAINCOAT.
HE'S SOMEHOW REPELLING IT
AND PUSHING IT
INTO ALL OF THIS BLOOD.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
HIS SKIN IS ACTING
LIKE A GROUND.
SOMEHOW, IT'S BEHAVING
JUST LIKE STRAIZO'S SCARF.
Santviento: MY BODY AND HIS BODY
SEEM TO BE REPELLING
AGAINST ONE OTHER.
( JoJo yelps )
( screams )
WHAT‐‐WHAT HAVE YOU
DONE TO MY HAND?!
( both gasp )
JoJo: WAIT. IT'S...
STILL THERE.
( both gasp )
JoJo: BUT CHECK IT OUT.
I CAN COMPLETELY REMOVE
MY THUMB.
DOESN'T ANYONE HAVE
A SENSE OF HUMOR LEFT?
COME ON, GUYS.
THIS IS FUNNY STUFF HERE.
♪
BUT SERIOUSLY, FOLKS.
LUCKY THING I ROLLED
MY WRIST JUST IN TIME.
THE BEAST'S IMMUNE TO HAMON.
( growls )
Speedwagon:
THAT'S NOT TRUE, JOJO.
DON'T YOU SEE?
IT WAS HAMON
THAT WAS PROTECTING YOU.
IT KEPT YOUR BODY
FROM BEING COMPLETELY ABSORBED
INTO THAT THING.
Von Stroheim: IDIOT! IT'S LIKE
EATING A BLOWFISH FOR HIM.
HE'S KNOWS HE MUST KILL IT FIRST
UND THEN REMOVE
THE POISON PARTS.
THAT IS HOW SANTVIENTO PLANS
ON ABSORBING JOJO'S BODY.
JoJo: WELL, TOO BAD FOR HIM
I'M NOT A BLOWFISH.
REGARDLESS, I NEED TO THINK
OF SOMETHING FAST HERE.
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO MAKE
MY EMERGENCY ESCAPE.
Von Stroheim: YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
THE DANGER OF SANTVIENTO
ESCAPING IS TOO HIGH.
‐ NO ONE LEAVES UNTIL HE'S DEAD!
‐ JoJo: AH, SHUT UP!
YOU RELEASED THIS MONSTER,
AND NOW YOU'RE SAYING
YOU NEED SOMEONE ELSE
TO CLEAN UP THE MESS?
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING ELSE
ON MY PLATE, VON STROHEIM.
( gasps )
( grunts )
LET'S SEE IF I CAN INJECT
SOME HAMON INTO HIS SYSTEM
WITH SOMETHING SHARP.
( gasps ) HIS SKIN
IS MALLEABLE LIKE RUBBER.
SEE IF YOU CAN DODGE THIS ONE,
BIG GUY!
HOW ABOUT A DOSE OF HAMON
RIGHT IN THE EYE?!
I HOPE YOU'RE READY
FOR YOUR CAN'T‐MISS CLOSE‐UP.
WHAT? THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
EVEN HIS EYES FEEL LIKE
THEY'RE SOME KIND OF RUBBER.
Speedwagon: JOJO,
GET OUT OF THERE RIGHT NOW!
( JoJo gasps, groans )
Speedwagon: JOJO!
Von Stroheim: THAT HIT
TO THE SOLAR PLEXUS
COMPLETELY KNOCKED
THE WIND OUT OF HIM.
Santviento: HMM.
HE SEEMS TO CREATE
HIS OWN ENERGY.
HE CONTROLS IT
WITH HIS BREATHING.
BUT LYING THERE NOW UNCONSCIOUS,
HE IS AS VULNERABLE
AS ANY OTHER HUMAN.
Speedwagon: JOJO! YOU'VE GOT
TO USE YOUR HAMON BREATHING!
‐ ( crack )
‐ ( screams )
YOU'VE GOT TO BREATHE! OHH!
USE YOUR HAMON BREATHING!
BREATHE, DAMN IT! BREATHE!
Von Stroheim: NO,
THERE'S NO STOPPING HIM.
I'VE GOT TO INITIATE
THE SELF‐DESTRUCT SEQUENCE.
( breathing heavily )
FOR THE FATHERLAND
UND FOR ETERNAL GLO‐‐
JoJo: I WOULDN'T DO THAT
IF I WERE YOU.
EVERYONE JUST CALM DOWN HERE.
LOOKS LIKE MY GAMBLE PAID OFF.
FIGURING THAT ATTACKS
FROM OUTSIDE ARE NO GOOD,
I'M GOING TO SEND
SOME HAMON INTO HIM
WHILE HE TRIES
TO ENJOY HIS MEAL.
Speedwagon: JOJO!
JoJo: I WAITED FOR YOU
TO START DEVOURING ME.
THIS IS GONNA BE FUN.
ENJOY YOUR HAMON BLAST!
♪
( JoJo panting )
I‐‐I THINK I GET IT.
NOW THAT I'VE SEEN HIM
FROM THE INSIDE, I UNDERSTAND.
HIS WHOLE BODY
IS ONE BIG DIGESTIVE SYSTEM.
EVERY ONE OF HIS CELLS,
THEY'RE ALL FILLED WITH
AGGRESSIVE DIGESTIVE ENZYMES,
MAKING IT POSSIBLE
TO DISSOLVE HIS PREY.
IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S ABSORBING THEM,
WHEN ACTUALLY
HE'S DIGESTING THEM WHOLE.
HAMON. THAT WAS WHAT
KEPT ME FROM BEING DIGESTED.
I SENT IT INSIDE HIM
WHEN HE TRIED TO EAT ME.
Speedwagon: JOJO,
YOUR HAMON WASN'T ENOUGH.
YOU HAVE TO FIND A WAY TO
COMPLETELY DESTROY SANTVIENTO.
( gasps )
( Santviento grunts )
♪
JoJo: THE SEPARATED PARTS
OF SANTVIENTO
ARE TRYING TO CONNECT
TO ONE ANOTHER.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH EXACTLY
WHAT HAPPENED WITH STRAIZO.
LUCKY ME, I FIGURED
YOU WOULD TRY TO GO
AND DO THE SAME THING.
VON STROHEIM!
( Von Stroheim shuddering )
AAH!
JoJo: COME ON!
GET AHOLD OF YOURSELF!
DOES THIS THING
HAVE ANY WEAKNESSES?
Von Stroheim: UH, SUNLIGHT!
JA, THAT'S IT.
IT WAS THERE ON THE WALLS
OF THE CAVE.
SUNLIGHT IS HIS NATURAL ENEMY.
THE VERY REASON HE MADE
THE MASKS IN THE FIRST PLACE
WAS TO CONQUER THE SUN.
JoJo: HMM.
( grunts )
Von Stroheim: ARE YOU INSANE?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
YOU CAN'T LET SANTVIENTO
ESCAPE INTO THE OUTSIDE WORLD!
JoJo: ON THE CONTRARY,
I THINK HE NEEDS TO GO
ON A NICE SUNLIT STROLL.
( grunting )
Speedwagon:
HE'S RUNNING OUT OF BREATH.
HE WON'T BE ABLE
TO CONTROL HIS HAMON.
HE HASN'T HAD
ENOUGH TRAINING WITH IT.
THIS FIGHT HAS
COMPLETELY EXHAUSTED HIM.
Santviento:
CEASE THIS FOOLISHNESS NOW,
YOU LOWLY PRIMITIVE.
( yells )
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( Santviento chuckles )
Speedwagon: REMEMBER, YOU MUST
CONTROL YOUR HAMON BREATHING!
JoJo: IF I COULD BREATHE,
I PROBABLY WOULDN'T BE
SO TIRED IN THE FIRST PLACE.
COME ON, BIG GUY.
I THINK WE'VE ALL HAD
JUST ABOUT ENOUGH OF YOU.
BUT FORTUNATELY FOR ME,
WE'RE JUST A FEW STEPS AWAY
FROM THE TWO OF US
CATCHING SOME NICE RAYS.
( grunting )
‐ ( thump )
‐ ( gasps )
WHAT THE HELL?
( crackling )
I CAN'T MOVE.
I FEEL SO HEAVY.
WHAT‐‐WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
Narrator: MEAT INVADE,
ALSO KNOWN AS FOUL FLESH.
JoJo: THEY'RE PIECES
OF HIS FLESH.
THEY'RE‐‐THEY'RE FEEDING ON ME.
( groans ) YOU‐‐YOU SON OF A‐‐
( groans )
GOT TO STAY FOCUSED.
Santviento: I NEVER ONCE
IMAGINED A HUMAN SUCH AS YOU
WOULD BE BORN
DURING MY SLUMBER.
( Von Stroheim gasping )
( Speedwagon gasps )
♪
WHAT?
Von Stroheim: JOESTAR,
LEAVE THE REST TO ME,
COLONEL RUDOL VON STROHEIM.
OPENING THE DOOR
WILL END ALL THIS.
ALLOW ME TO HELP YOU DESTROY
THIS VILE CREATURE.
JoJo: WOW, VON STROHEIM.
I WOULD HAVE NEVER THOUGHT...
( cracking )
Santviento: HUMPH.
WELL ATTEMPTED, PRIMITIVES.
( Von Stroheim screaming )
I CAN ALMOST REACH THE DOOR.
( groaning )
Santviento:
A MEANINGLESS STRUGGLE. HUMPH.
( Von Stroheim screams )
JoJo: THIS IS BAD.
Von Stroheim: JOESTAR, GET UP.
DON'T JUST LIE THERE
LIKE A BABY.
JoJo: I'M TRYING TO THINK HERE.
IF YOU HADN'T NOTICED,
WE'RE BOTH IN DEEP TROUBLE.
Von Stroheim: SILENCE!
DO YOU SEE THOSE AXES
ON THE WALL NEXT TO YOU?
REACH UP, UND GRAB ONE.
TAKE ONE, UND CHOP OFF MY LEG!
JoJo: I‐‐I CAN'T DO THAT!
Von Stroheim: YOU COWARD,
CUT OFF MY LEG.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
WE'RE GETTING THAT DOOR OPEN.
JoJo: MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT,
BUT ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
I MEAN, THERE HAS GOT TO BE
SOME OTHER WAY.
Von Stroheim: DO AS I SAY!
HE'S RECOVERING, JOESTAR.
JoJo: BUT I'M NO DOCTOR.
I'VE NO IDEA
HOW TO DO THIS RIGHT.
Von Stroheim:
I AM A PROUD SERVANT
OF THE WEHRMACHT!
I AM PREPARED TO DO
WHATEVER IS REQUIRED
TO FULFILL MY DUTY!
I PROUDLY GIVE UP MY LEG
FOR THE FATHERLAND!
NOW HURRY UP
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
DAMN IT! DO IT NOW, JOESTAR!
JoJo: OKAY, I'LL DO IT.
IF YOU REALLY WANT ME TO
CHOP IT OFF, THEN OFF IT GOES.
Von Stroheim: I DEMAND
THAT YOU CHOP IT OFF NOW!
JoJo: I FIGURED THIS GUY WAS
JUST SOME BLOATED POWERMONGER,
BUT I GOTTA HAND IT TO HIM.
HE'S GOT GUTS.
I WISH THERE WERE
SOME OTHER WAY.
BUT IF HE'S
COURAGEOUS ENOUGH, THEN...
FORGIVE ME! ( yells )
( Von Stroheim gasping )
( yells )
( Santviento gasps )
( screaming )
JoJo: TELL ME, BIG GUY, HOW DOES
THAT SUNSHINE FEEL ON YOUR SKIN?
( Santviento screaming )
Von Stroheim: WE DID IT.
( cracking )
JoJo: WHAT'S HE DOING?
( gasps )
( Von Stroheim screams )
HELP ME!
THAT MONSTER IS TRYING
TO CRAWL INSIDE MY LEG!
JoJo: GET OUTTA THERE, YOU!
WHOA. THIS IS A SHOCK.
VON STROHEIM'S BASICALLY OKAY,
AND HE'S FREE OF ANY HAMON.
‐ ( thump )
‐ HUH?
( Von Stroheim gasping )
DAMN IT, YOU GET OUT OF ME,
SANTVIENTO!
JoJo: I‐‐I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS THING'S WILLPOWER.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
IF HE STAYS INSIDE VON STROHEIM,
HE'LL BE TOTALLY FINE
EVEN HERE IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
Von Stroheim: I CAN FEEL HIM.
THIS CAN'T BE REAL.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
THE WORST PART ABOUT THIS IS?
MY LEG DOESN'T
EVEN HURT ANYMORE.
IT FEELS PLEASANT.
YOU BELIEVE THAT?
‐ ( groaning )
‐ JoJo: MY GOD.
VON STROHEIM!
♪
( gasps )
( Von Stroheim groaning )
JoJo: WAIT. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PUT IT DOWN, VON STROHEIM.
Von Stroheim: STAY BACK!
YOU'VE SEEN WHAT HORRIBLE THINGS
SANTVIENTO IS CAPABLE OF!
THERE IS NO HOPE!
MY DESTINY HAS BEEN DETERMINED!
SO NOW ALL I CAN DO
IS DESTROY THE BOTH OF US!
BUT I HAVE ONE MORE THING TO SAY
TO YOU BEFORE MY TIME IS DONE.
IF YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD FOR YOU,
YOU LISTEN CLOSE, ENGLISHMAN.
OUR WEHRMACHT, WE‐‐
WE DID NOT AWAKEN SANTVIENTO
SIMPLY FOR SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH
OR MILITARY GAIN.
JoJo: THEN WHY?
WHY DID YOU RISK IT? TELL ME!
Von Stroheim: SILENCE!
IT'S YOUR DESTINY
TO HEAR THESE WORDS
FROM MY LIPS, JOESTAR!
SANTVIENTO IS JUST
THE TIP OF THE ICEBERG.
THE WEHRMACHT HAS DISCOVERED
ANOTHER PILLAR IN EUROPE. AGH!
WE NOW KNOW THAT SANTVIENTO
IS NOT THE ONLY ONE
OF HIS KIND AROUND.
( gasps, screams )
JoJo: WAIT.
SO THERE'S MORE OF THEM?!
WHERE ARE THEY?
TELL ME, VON STROHEIM! WHERE?
Von Stroheim: I'M SORRY,
BUT I DON'T HAVE THAT ANSWER
FOR YOU, JOESTAR.
THERE ARE
MORE PILLAR MEN OUT THERE,
UND THEY HAVE POWERS THAT ARE
BEYOND OUR WILDEST IMAGINATION.
FOR MILLENNIA, THOSE POWERS
HAVE REMAINED DORMANT,
BUT THAT WON'T LAST,
UND SOON THEY WILL AWAKEN.
YOU MUST FIND ANOTHER WEAKNESS
OTHER THAN JUST SUNLIGHT,
OR ELSE HOPE IS LOST.
THAT'S WHY WE WERE
EXPERIMENTING ON SANTVIENTO.
WE WERE LOOKING
FOR THAT WEAKNESS.
THERE'S A BATTLE AGAINST
THE PILLAR MEN YET TO BE FOUGHT.
THE EVENTS OF 50 YEARS AGO
CALL UPON YOU FOR THAT BATTLE.
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU WILL NEED MORE THAN JUST
YOUR HAMON TO OVERCOME THEM.
YOU MUST GO TO ROME!
THERE YOU WILL FIND
SOMEONE WHO CAN HELP YOU!
IT IS SOMEONE THAT
YOUR SPEEDWAGON KNOWS VERY WELL.
( grunts )
SANTVIENTO IS
TRYING TO MOVE MY BODY
INTO THAT WELL
SO HE CAN HIDE AGAIN.
BUT HE CAN'T STOP ME FROM
OPENING UP MY BODY COMPLETELY
TO LET THE SUN SHINE IN.
( spits )
JoJo: VON STROHEIM...
DON'T YOU DARE.
( Von Stroheim laughs )
"HUMAN GREATNESS LIES
IN HAVING THE COURAGE
TO FACE DOWN ONE'S FEARS."
DO YOU KNOW WHO SAID THAT?
THE GREEK HISTORIAN PLUTARCH.
( JoJo gasps )
Von Stroheim: FAREWELL...
YOU ANNOYING ENGLISHMAN!
JoJo: DON'T DO IT!
I STILL HAVE QUESTIONS FOR YOU!
VON STROHEIM!
( groans )
DAMN THAT CRAZY GERMAN
AND ALL HIS HONOR.
( groans )
I'M SURE THAT WE COULD HAVE
FOUND ANOTHER WAY.
( sighs )
( gasps )
♪
( cracking )
SANTVIENTO!
Santviento:
YOU ANNOY ME, PRIMITIVE.
I WILL DESTROY YOU!
JoJo: STEADY YOUR BREATHING.
USE YOUR HAMON TECHNIQUE.
( deep breaths )
( Santviento growls )
( JoJo growls )
( screams )
Santviento: PRIMITIVE,
WHY OPPOSE ME?
YOU WERE DOOMED HERE
FROM THE START.
JoJo: HAH!
I KNOW JUST WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO SAY NEXT.
YOU'LL SAY, "I'VE SEEN
RIGHT THROUGH YOU
ALL THIS TIME, JOESTAR."
Santviento:
I'VE SEEN RIGHT THROUGH YOU
ALL THIS TIME, JOESTAR.
( gasps )
( screams )
JoJo: IT'S HIGH NOON
OVER THIS WELL.
THE SUN REFLECTING
OFF OF THE WATER
SHOULD COOK YOU NICELY,
ALTHOUGH I DOUBT
YOU EVEN THOUGHT OF THAT.
YOU WERE THINKING ABOUT JUMPING
UNDER THE NICE COOL WATER
AND GETTING
OUT OF THE SUN, RIGHT?
( deep breath )
WELL, SCREW THAT IDEA.
I'M NOT LETTING YOU
TOUCH THE WATER!
( grunting )
( screams )
♪
( JoJo sighs )
I'M ALIVE, THANKS TO THE SUN.
HE'S A STATUE NOW.
BUT WE FINALLY GOT THAT SMILE.
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Man: MY GRANDFATHER
DIED TRAGICALLY.
JoJo: YOU COULDN'T EVEN
BEAT ONE OF THOSE PIGEONS.
Officer: QUICKLY!
BRING OUT MORE U. V. LAMPS!
Pillar Man: NOW IS THE TIME.
AWAKEN, MY MASTERS!