JoJo: DOWN HERE,
MY HAMON WILL HIT YOU
ALL THE HARDER.
UNDERWATER
TURQUOISE BLUE OVERDRIVE!
( Blueford yells )
Speedwagon: HE DID IT!
‐ Zeppeli: BRAVO.
‐ ( Tarukus grunts )
Poco: THAT WAS AMAZING.
JoJo: IT'S NOT OVER YET!
I CAN'T BELIEVE BLUEFORD
WAS ABLE TO DODGE
THAT BLAST OF HAMON.
HE MOVES SO FAST UNDERWATER.
HE WAS ALL A BLUR.
MY OVERDRIVE
BARELY GLANCED OFF HIS FOREHEAD.
NOW I KNOW ANYTHING LESS
THAN A SOLID PUNCH
WON'T BE ENOUGH
TO SEND THE HAMON INTO HIM.
Blueford: MY GOOD LORD DIO,
I THANK THEE FOR THIS LIFE ANEW
THAT I MAY DUEL
WITH THIS STOUTHEARTED LAD.
MY HEART WOULD SWELL TO BURSTING
IF STILL IT BEAT.
IN BLOOD AND DEED,
HE IS THE STUFF OF HEROES.
NOW WE WILL FIGHT
IN OUR NATIVE ELEMENT.
IT IS BY MASTERY OF OUR ARTS
AND STRENGTH OF OUR SPIRITS
THAT WE WAGE THIS DUEL.
BARE YOUR SOUL.
HOLD NOTHING BACK,
LEST YOU NOT SURVIVE
BEYOND THIS MOMENT!
( yells )
JoJo: EVEN AS DIO'S PUPPET,
HIS PRIDE IS A FORCE
TO BE RECKONED WITH,
BUT HIS KNIGHTLY VALOR
HAS BEEN TWISTED
INTO A WANTON LOVE OF VIOLENCE.
Blueford: WHEN I BEST YOU,
I'LL TAKE YOUR HEAD
AS MY TROPHY!
JoJo: IT'S EASY TO LET
YOUR HAIR DO THE WORK.
COME. WITHSTAND MY HAMON
FACE TO FACE LIKE A MAN!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
JoJo: OVERDRIVE BARRAGE!
( grunting )
( screams )
Zeppeli: JOJO!
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
HAMON CAN ONLY BE PROJECTED
THROUGH THE ARMS AND THE LEGS.
WITH HIS ARMS BOUND
IN FRONT OF HIM LIKE THAT,
HE HAS NO WAY OF BLASTING
THROUGH THAT INFERNAL HAIR
OF BLUEFORD'S.
Speedwagon:
I‐I WANNA HELP HIM OUT,
BUT YOU AND ME
HAVE GOT THINGS EVEN WORSE.
I THINK OL' TARUKUS
FANCIES A DUST‐UP.
( JoJo screaming )
HIS HAIR,
IT'S TEARING THROUGH MY CLOTHES.
THROUGH MY SKIN.
THE MORE I STRUGGLE,
THE TIGHTER IT WINDS,
AND IT'S SUCKING MY BLOOD AWAY.
( grunting )
Blueford:
BID YOUR PETTY LIFE ADIEU.
BEHOLD, THE COUP DE GR ÂCE!
I'LL TAKE YOUR HEAD
AND BATHE IN A FOUNTAIN
OF LIFE‐GIVING BLOOD!
JoJo: TAKE THIS!
( inhales )
♪
WATER'S NOT ALL
THAT CONDUCTS HAMON.
METAL SILVER OVERDRIVE!
‐ ( Tarukus grunts )
‐ Speedwagon: WHAT A BRAIN.
USING THE SWORD
TO HOIST BLUEFORD
BY HIS OWN BLEEDING PETARD.
WHO THINKS OF THAT?
JoJo: HOW MY HEART RESONATES.
I'M PULSING WITH HEAT AND LIFE.
( breathes deeply )
MY VERY BLOOD
IS A SYMPHONY WITHIN ME!
SUNLIGHT YELLOW OVERDRIVE!
( Blueford groans )
‐ ( Zeppeli gasps )
‐ Speedwagon: THERE WE GO.
THAT'S IT. ABOUT TIME WE HEARD
THE WELCOME CRACKLE OF HAMON.
( JoJo exhales )
WHEN I PUMMELED BLUEFORD
A MOMENT AGO,
SOMETHING FELT DIFFERENT.
KNOWING HIS PAST
MAKES HIS PRESENT CORRUPTION
ALL THE WORSE.
TAKE HEART, JOJO.
HE IS THAT MAN NO LONGER.
HE'S NOTHING BUT A ZOMBIE
EAGER TO SPREAD HIS EVIL.
YOU MUST BE THE ONE TO END HIM.
( sizzling )
Blueford: I AM
THE BLACK KNIGHT BLUEFORD.
STRIKE ME AS THOU WILT.
THIS PAIN IS NOTHING!
Speedwagon:
HE'S STILL DANGEROUS, MATE!
LOOK OUT!
EVEN MISSING AN ARM
AND SCORCHED ALL TO HELL,
HE'S LAYING INTO JOJO
EVERY BIT AS FEROCIOUSLY.
( both gasp )
Speedwagon: WHAT THE?!
DON'T JUST STAND THERE!
DO SOMETHING!
IF YOU DON'T GET OUTTA THERE
NOW, IT'S CURTAINS FOR YOU!
HAVE THEY BOTH GONE MAD?
WHAT ARE THEY DOIN', EH?
( sizzling )
JoJo: A MOMENT AGO,
YOU SAID,
"THIS PAIN IS NOTHING."
THAT MEANS PAIN IS SOMETHING
YOU CAN FEEL AGAIN.
♪
( Zeppeli gasps )
THE FLOWERS,
THEY'RE BLOOMING
ALL AROUND HIM.
EVEN NOW, THE HAMON
RAVAGES THE EVIL
THAT ANIMATES
BLUEFORD'S LONG‐DEAD CORPSE.
YOU SEE? THE LONG‐FORGOTTEN PAIN
CAME BACK.
ONLY HUMANS KNOW
THAT SORT OF ACHE.
OBSERVE, MY DEAR SPEEDWAGON.
HIS ZOMBIE BODY
SUCCUMBS TO THE HAMON,
BUT HIS NOBLE SOUL
IS REDEEMED IN THE PROCESS.
JoJo: I COULD SENSE
THE GOOD IN YOU.
THAT'S WHY
I DIDN'T TRY TO DODGE.
YOU COULD HAVE
KILLED ME JUST NOW,
BUT YOU STAYED YOUR HAND.
Speedwagon: LOOK AT HIS FACE.
IT'S LIKE ALL THE RAGE
AND HATRED HE HAD
WHEN DIO BROUGHT HIM BACK
ARE GONE.
HIS FEATURES ARE SO GENTLE,
HE COULD BE A BLOKE CATCHING UP
WITH HIS OLDEST MATE.
Blueford: YOU STOOD THERE
LIKE A STATUE,
READY TO TAKE THE FATAL BLOW.
OBLIVION BECKONED,
BUT YOU PUT YOUR TRUST IN ME.
YOUR FAITH IN HUMAN GOODNESS
IS RARE.
( coughs )
( chuckles )
ONCE I'D HAVE RAILED
AGAINST THE PAIN I FEEL.
NOW, GOING TO MY RIGHTFUL END,
I CHERISH
ALL THAT PROVES ME HUMAN.
IT GIVES ME JOY.
THE EMBERS DULL WITHIN ME,
BUT I AM TRANQUIL.
THERE IS NO BITTERNESS LEFT.
WHAT IRONY TO LIVE YET AGAIN,
DYING WITH THANKS ON MY LIPS
FOR THE VERY MAN
WHO SLAUGHTERS ME ANEW.
I SHALL RETURN
TO MY ONE TRUE MASTER.
I WOULD KNOW THE NAME
OF THE WARRIOR WHO BESTED ME.
WOULD YOU KINDLY
DO ME THAT HONOR?
JoJo: IT'S JONATHAN JOESTAR.
Blueford: SIR JONATHAN,
I LEAVE YOU THIS SWORD,
GIVEN TO ME
BY MY PRECIOUS QUEEN,
AND THE WORD ENGRAVED UPON IT.
LUCK.
BUT FIRST. LET ME AFFIX
MY OWN BENEDICTION.
PLUCK.
JoJo: SIR BLUEFORD.
Blueford: HEH.
JoJo: GO YOU TO YOUR REST.
LET NO ONE DOUBT
YOU HAVE EARNED IT, BLUEFORD.
WHY? WHY DID I HAVE TO STRIKE
HIM DOWN TO REDEEM HIS SOUL?
HE DIED ONCE BEFORE
WITH HATE IN HIS HEART,
BUT HIS SPIRIT WAS STILL PURE.
HE RETURNED NOT OUT OF CHOICE,
BUT DRAGGED ABOVE BY DIO'S EVIL,
HIS EVIL AND THE MASK'S POWER.
I WILL SEND THEM BOTH TO HELL
BEFORE THE DAWN!
Speedwagon: JOJO,
HE'S RIGHT BEHIND YOU!
( JoJo gasps )
TARUKUS!
( Tarukus scoffs )
‐ ( hisses )
‐ JoJo: YOU VILLAIN!
THAT WAS THE ARMOR OF
A STEADFAST FRIEND AND COMRADE.
HE DIED WITH HONOR AND DIGNITY.
Tarukus: HE DIED
LIKE A SPINELESS DOG!
HE WAS TOO CLEVER BY HALF,
LIKED WINNING HIS FIGHTS
WITH THINKING.
I JUST HIT 'EM
UNTIL THEY FALL TO PIECES!
WHAT USE HAVE I GOT FOR CLEVER?
I CARRY A SWORD
AS TALL AS A MAN.
NONE OF YOU
WILL GET AN EASY DEATH.
( roars )
♪
( Poco gasping )
( screams )
♪
Zeppeli: JOJO, NICE CATCH.
Speedwagon:
THE CLIFF IS CRUMBLING!
Zeppeli: HMM.
THESE DEAD LEAVES.
JOJO!
JoJo: YES, SIR.
( both inhale )
LIFE MAGNETISM OVERDRIVE!
( Tarukus growls )
( roars )
JoJo: HURRY, POCO, SPEEDWAGON!
GRAB ON!
Narrator: ALL HUMAN BEINGS,
WHETHER ADEPT AT HAMON OR NOT,
CONSTANTLY EXUDE
A WEAK MAGNETIC FIELD.
AN OVERDRIVE CAN INCREASE
THE POWER OF THAT FIELD.
JOJO AND ZEPPELI
SENT IT INTO THE LEAVES,
DRAWING THEM TOGETHER
INTO A SOLID SHEET.
Poco: W‐WOW.
BYE.
( laughs )
( Tarukus growls )
Poco: WE'RE FLYING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I BET YOU'RE MAGICIANS, HUH?
YOU'D HAVE TO BE, RIGHT?
HOW DID YOU LEARN TO DO
ALL OF THESE NEAT SPELLS
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
Speedwagon: DAMN GOOD QUESTION.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING 'EM DO IT,
AND I STILL PINCH MYSELF.
OI, BARON, WHAT'S THE STORY?
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
HOW ON EARTH DID YOU PICK UP
ALL THIS MUMBO JUMBO?
( seabirds calling )
♪
Zeppeli: MANY YEARS AGO,
MY TRAVELS TOOK ME TO INDIA,
WHERE I DISCOVERED
A MYSTERIOUS MAN.
HE CALLED HIMSELF A DOCTOR,
THOUGH HE WAS VERY YOUNG
AND LACKED
ALL THE TOOLS OF THE TRADE.
LITTLE DID I KNOW
HE WAS MORE POTENT OF A MEDIC
THAN I'D EVER ENCOUNTERED.
HE TOOK A GANGRENOUS LIMB
IN HIS HANDS
AND HEALED IT
WITH LIGHT FROM WITHIN.
THAT WAS THE DAY
I LEARNED OF HAMON.
I'D BEEN LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
WITH WHICH TO FIGHT
THE STONE MASK'S EVIL,
AND IN HAMON, I HAD FOUND IT.
EAGER TO LEARN,
I CROSSED INTO TIBET
AND UP THE SALWEEN RIVER
IN SEARCH OF HE
WHO HAD TAUGHT THE YOUNG HEALER.
HIS NAME WAS TONPETTY.
( Zeppeli gasps )
Tonpetty: STRANGER, THESE EYES
OF MINE HAVE SEEN YOUR FUTURE.
IF YOU PURSUE THE MYSTERIES
OF HAMON AS MY PUPIL,
YOUR FATE IS SEALED.
THE DAY WILL COME WHEN THIS
WILL BE THE DEATH OF YOU.
Zeppeli: I UNDERSTAND.
IF I MUST DIE TO END THIS QUEST,
SO BE IT.
♪
( Hamon crackling )
MASTER TONPETTY'S PROPHECY
IS NEVER FAR FROM MY MIND,
BUT I CANNOT TELL THEM,
NOT EVEN JOJO.
Speedwagon: BARON...
( whooshing )
SO THAT SOUND,
THAT'S PART OF HAMON
DOING ITS THING, YEAH?
( JoJo gasps ) HARDLY.
Poco: LOOK OUT! IT'S TARUKUS!
( Tarukus roars )
Zeppeli: HE'S INSANE,
LEAPING FROM THAT HEIGHT
JUST TO GIVE CHASE TO HIS FOES.
THERE'S A GOODLY AMOUNT OF HAMON
HOLDING THESE LEAVES TOGETHER,
YOU BRUTE,
PAINFUL TO THE TOUCH
FOR THE UNDEAD.
‐ JoJo: WHAT'S THAT?
‐ Poco: THAT'S WHERE THE KNIGHTS
USED TO TRAIN IN THE OLDEN DAYS.
JoJo: LEAP TO SAFETY, EVERYONE,
BEFORE WE GET
SWATTED OUT OF THE SKY!
( Poco yells )
Speedwagon: CRAZY BLIGHTER.
HE JUST SLAMMED HIMSELF
STRAIGHT INTO THE TOWER.
Zeppeli: YES,
AND THANK YOUR LUCKY STARS
THAT HE DID, SPEEDWAGON.
UNLIKE THEIR MASTER,
DIO'S MINIONS CAN'T REGENERATE,
SO THAT SHOULD BE THE LAST
WE SEE OF THAT BEAST.
( JoJo gasps )
♪
( Tarukus growls )
Zeppeli: HOW DID‐‐
HE SHOULD BE MINCEMEAT.
EVEN IN DEATH,
HE HAS A WILL OF IRON.
HOW DOES HIS BODY ENDURE
UNDER SUCH PUNISHMENT?
Speedwagon: HE'S CLIMBING UP.
Zeppeli: WE CAN'T DESTROY DIO
WHILE THIS MONSTER
DOGS OUR STEPS.
IT SEEMS WE HAVE
NO OTHER CHOICE.
TARUKUS MEETS HIS DOOM
HERE AND NOW.
JOJO, THIS WILL BE PERILOUS.
GET THE LAD TO SAFETY WITHIN.
( Tarukus growling )
( chuckles )
( clank )
( JoJo gasps )
THIS DOOR...
‐ SOMETHING'S ODD ABOUT IT.
‐ Poco: BE CAREFUL.
THIS IS WHERE THEY USED TO TRAIN
THE KNIGHTS HOW TO KILL PEOPLE.
THEY SAY
IT'S FULL OF BOOBY TRAPS.
( chain jangles )
Speedwagon: DUCK, JOJO!
SOMETHING'S COMING AT YA!
( JoJo gasps )
‐ Poco: OH, NO!
‐ Zeppeli: JOJO!
JoJo: WHO ENSNARED ME?
TARUKUS.
Tarukus: YES. CAUGHT YOU GOOD.
YOU'RE FLEET OF FOOT,
LITTLE MAN,
BUT NOW YOU AND ME
ARE CHAINED TO EACH OTHER.
YOU GOT NOWHERE TO RUN.
( JoJo gasps )
Narrator: JOJO HAD WANDERED
INTO THE LAIR
OF THE TWO‐HEADED DRAGON,
AN ANCIENT SPARRING GROUND AND
HOME OF THE CHAIN DEATH‐MATCH.
Tarukus: I KILLED 48 MEN HERE.
TAKING A LIFE'S AN ART FORM,
AND I'M A MASTER.
( Zeppeli grunting )
Speedwagon: THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU CAN'T PUNCH THROUGH IT.
THAT DOOR IS SOLID IRON.
Poco: GOODNESS. HE'S BATTERED
HIS KNUCKLES BLOODY AGAINST IT.
Zeppeli: HAMON IS
VERY VERSATILE,
BUT IT'S MEANT TO BE
USED AS A RAPIER,
NOT AS A SLEDGEHAMMER.
BRICKS I COULD BEAT TO A POWDER,
BUT THIS DOOR IS TOO STRONG.
JOJO FACES A DARKER DILEMMA.
THAT CHAIN ABOUT HIS NECK
IS MORE THAN RIPPLE ENERGY
CAN OVERCOME.
Tarukus: BREAKING OUT
OF THAT COLLAR IS IMPOSSIBLE,
AND YOU'LL NEED
THE KEY TO UNLOCK IT.
TOO BAD IT'S RIGHT HERE.
DURING A DEATH MATCH,
THE DOOR TO THE OUTSIDE
IS FASHIONED TO LOCK TIGHT.
JUST AS I HAVE THE KEY
TO YOUR COLLAR,
YOU HAVE THE ONE
THAT GOES TO MINE.
THEREFORE, THE ONLY WAY
THAT EITHER OF US
IS GOING TO GET OUT OF HERE...
( JoJo gags )
IS BY TAKING THE OTHER'S HEAD!
( JoJo yells )
OVERDRIVE!
( gasping )
THE CHAIN IS TOUCHING
THE STONE CEILING,
SO THE HAMON LACKS
A DIRECT PATH INTO TARUKUS.
( Tarukus growls )
( bone cracks )
JoJo: HE'S BROKEN
THE BONE IN MY FOREARM.
( gasps )
IT'S A SIMPLE THING TO FIX.
A LITTLE HAMON,
AND I'M GOOD AS NEW.
BUT IN ORDER TO USE HAMON,
I NEED TO BE FREE
OF THIS DAMNABLE COLLAR.
I CAN'T BREATHE.
( door rattles )
Zeppeli: JOJO!
Poco: OH, NO.
THIS IS ALL SO FRIGHTENING,
I THINK I WET MYSELF.
THIS VILLAGE WAS SAFE
UNTIL THESE MEN ARRIVED.
I'M IN DANGER HERE.
YOU NEED TO GET AWAY
FROM ALL THIS FIGHTING
ON THE DOUBLE, POCO.
Speedwagon: I SEE A LEVER,
BARON ZEPPELI.
NO TELLING FOR CERTAIN,
BUT I THINK PULLING ON IT
WILL OPEN THIS DOOR.
Zeppeli: FIGHTING TARUKUS
IS A DAUNTING ENOUGH TASK
AS IT IS,
NEVER MIND DOING IT FRESH
OUT OF A BATTLE WITH BLUEFORD.
( blood spurts )
COME HELL OR HIGH WATER,
WE MUST FIND A WAY
TO GET IN THERE AND HELP HIM.
Speedwagon: UHH! IT'S LOCKED UP
TIGHTER THAN A NUNNERY.
♪
Poco: IT'S SO NARROW.
TRY AS THEY MIGHT, THEY COULD
NEVER SQUEEZE THROUGH,
BUT...
MAYBE I COULD.
( Tarukus yells )
Zeppeli: BLAST IT!
WE COULD BATTER THIS DOOR
'TIL JUDGMENT DAY TO NO AVAIL.
WE'LL HAVE TO USE
THE CLIFFSIDE ENTRANCE
TARUKUS USED.
Speedwagon: BUT THAT'LL
TAKE TOO MUCH TIME,
TIME THAT HE DON'T GOT.
Zeppeli: I KNOW,
BUT WE'VE NO OTHER CHOICE.
( Speedwagon growls )
ALWAYS
ON THE BLEEDIN' SIDELINES.
I'M POWERLESS.
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO TO HELP.
Boy: LOOK AT ME, BRAT.
I'M TALKING TO YOU.
‐ ( Poco sobs )
‐ Boy: I SAID LOOK AT ME.
‐ ( boy #2 laughs )
‐ Boy: ARE YOU STUPID OR WHAT?
Boy #3: HE'S SUCH
A LITTLE SCAREDY‐CAT.
Boy #4: WHAT A BABY.
HE'S SHAKING LIKE A LEAF.
Boy #2: LOOK, FELLAS.
LOOK AT HIM.
Boy #1: AW,
IS THE BABY GONNA CRY?
( boys laughing )
Boy #2: HEY. LOOK.
Boy #1: HMM?
( boy #4 gasps ) COME ON!
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
Poco: SIS, IT'S YOU.
Sister: POCO, REALLY?
YOU'RE LETTING THOSE BOYS
BULLY YOU AGAIN?
THEY DO THIS ALL THE TIME.
WHY NOT TRY
STANDING UP TO THEM FOR ONCE?
Poco: I'LL BLOODY THEIR NOSES!
I WILL!
Sister: WHEN? TOMORROW?
IN A YEAR?
Poco: UH, I DON'T KNOW.
Sister: POCO...
WHAT FRIGHTENS YOU
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE?
( Poco yelps )
Sister: I KNOW THAT HURT,
BUT YOU'RE STILL IN ONE PIECE.
PAIN'S NOT THE WORST THING.
THERE'S SOMETHING FAR WORSE.
Poco: HUH?
Sister: IT'S GROWING UP
BEING TOO AFRAID TO DO ANYTHING.
WHAT KIND OF A LIFE
WOULD THAT BE?
Poco: I'M SORRY, SIS.
( sister sighs )
( Poco crying )
Sister: IT'S ALL RIGHT, POCO.
LET'S GET YOU HOME
AND INTO SOME CLEAN CLOTHES.
♪
( thump )
Zeppeli: POCO!
Speedwagon: A WINDOW.
OI, LAD! THAT'S BRAVE,
BUT GOIN' IN THERE
IS GONNA BE THE END OF YA!
Zeppeli: SPEEDWAGON,
GET THE BOY DOWN!
A BUTCHER LIKE TARUKUS
DOESN'T CARE WHO HE KILLS!
HE'LL CRUSH POCO UNDERFOOT
LIKE A BUG!
Speedwagon: COME ON, NOW!
ENOUGH OF THIS NONSENSE, POCO!
Poco: JUST THINK OF WHAT'S
GONNA HAPPEN TO WIND KNIGHTS LOT
IF THESE MONSTERS WIN.
IF THAT JOJO GUY GETS KILLED
IN HERE, THEY'LL ATTACK US NEXT.
WHAT IF THEY HURT SIS?
( bell jingles )
I HAVE TO KEEP HER SAFE,
NO MATTER WHAT.
HEY, SIS!
I'M STANDING UP TO THEM NOW!
JoJo: STAY BACK! HE'LL KILL YOU.
( Tarukus growls )
DO NOT INTERFERE, YOU BRAT!
( JoJo roars )
( both scream )
JoJo: POCO!
Poco: IT HURT A LOT,
BUT I'M STILL IN ONE PIECE,
SO IT'S FINE.
♪
( lock clicks )
I WAS BRAVE, HUH?
( laughs )
Speedwagon:
BRAVE AS A BEAR, MY LAD.
TAKE HEART.
IT'S NOTHING THAT WON'T HEAL.
GET HIM, BARON! GO!
GIVE THAT HULKING BASTARD
THE WHAT‐FOR.
♪
ZEPPELI?
Tonpetty: THE DAY WILL COME
WHEN THIS WILL BE
THE DEATH OF YOU.
Zeppeli: INFINE.
IS TONIGHT THE NIGHT
THAT I GO TO MY GRAVE?
( Speedwagon gasps )
Zeppeli: FATE IS
A FICKLE MISTRESS,
BUT I CANNOT DENY HER.
Speedwagon: ZEPPELI...
WHY DO YOU SOUND SO DIRE?
( Tarukus growls )
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Speedwagon: THIS BLOODY SAVAGERY
IS UNBELIEVABLE!
JoJo: OH, NO! TARAKUS!
Tarakus: PATHETIC
WASTE OF FLESH!
Zeppeli: JOJO, TAKE IT!
MAKE IT YOURS!