♪
JoJo: WHAT THE HECK
IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE?
YOU THINK YOU'RE FUNNY,
PUTTING BLACK INK
ALL OVER MY SPAGHETTI,
IS THAT RIGHT?
Waiter: N‐N‐NO, SIR, NOT AT ALL.
THIS IS CALLED
AL NERO DI SEPPIA.
IT IS A CLASSIC PASTA DISH
MADE WITH FRESH SQUID INK,
HENCE THE COLOR.
JoJo: REALLY?
Waiter: IT'S QUITE DELICIOUS.
JoJo: HMM.
Man: HMM.
( gasps )
SAY, THIS IS DELICIOUS!
MMM. ( slurps )
MM‐MM‐MM.
Man: THIS HOTEL USED TO BE
A PLACE OF CLASS AND REFINEMENT.
NOW THEY LET
JUST ANYONE IN HERE.
SIGNORINA, ACCEPT THIS,
A TOKEN OF YOUR BEAUTY.
Woman: IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
Man: NOT AS MUCH AS YOU.
WHEN YOU REMOVE THIS AT NIGHT,
PLEASE THINK OF ME,
AND WE SHALL BE TOGETHER
IN YOUR DREAMS.
JoJo: COME ON!
DID THAT MOZZARELLA CHEESE‐BALL
JUST SAY WHAT I THINK HE SAID?!
I DIDN'T KNOW EAVESDROPPING
COULD ROT YOUR TEETH.
Man: I SHALL CAST
AN ENCHANTMENT UPON IT,
JUST A LITTLE LOVE SPELL,
AND THEN YOU WILL HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO FALL TO MY PASSION.
( kiss )
( JoJo shrieks )
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
THIS GUY IS MAKING ME SICK.
( man scoffs )
AND I SHALL SPREAD
MY CHARM'S MAGIC
TO THOSE DELICIOUS LIPS
OF YOURS.
JoJo: THAT'S JUST RIDICULOUS.
HOW COULD ANY MODERN WOMAN FALL
FOR SUCH AN OBVIOUS ACT?
DISGUSTING.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
( breathes deeply )
HAMON DI SEPPIA.
THIS SHOULD STICK
TO THAT LITTLE CASANOVA'S
ENCHANTING FACE FOR A BIT.
( chuckles )
( gasps )
HOW‐‐HOW DID HE JUST DO THAT?
( slurps )
THAT‐‐THAT WAS HAMON.
YES, I'M SURE OF IT.
Waiter: PARDON THE INTRUSION.
BUT THERE IS A PHONE CALL
FROM A MR. SPEEDWAGON,
MR. CAESAR ZEPPELI.
Caesar: MAMMA MIA.
I WILL BE RIGHT THERE.
JoJo: WHAT? WHAT THE‐‐
THAT SPAGHETTI‐BRAINED WOMANIZER
IS THE CAESAR ZEPPELI WE CAME
ALL THE WAY HERE TO FIND?!
( Caesar chuckles )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Narrator: THIS IS
THE SPEEDWAGON FOUNDATION.
THIS COMPLEX
WAS BUILT 28 YEARS AGO
WITH FUNDS FROM
THE AMPLE SPEEDWAGON FORTUNE.
HERE, ALL MANNERS OF SCIENCE,
MEDICINE, ARCHAEOLOGY, AND MORE
ARE GENEROUSLY FUNDED
AND EXHAUSTIVELY RESEARCHED
FOR THE BENEFIT
OF ALL HUMANKIND.
BUT THE FOUNDATION
ALSO HOUSES A DARKER PURPOSE...
ONE TO UNLOCK THE SECRET
OF THE STONE MASKS.
Researcher: THE U. V. LIGHTS
ARE VERY POWERFUL.
PLEASE, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
Researcher #2:
INTRODUCE THE SNAKE.
( snake hissing )
( researchers gasp )
( blood whooshes )
Researcher #3:
IT WAS ABSORBED INTO THE STONE!
Researcher #4:
SANTVIENTO STILL ISN'T DEAD.
HIS BODY IS
DEFENDING ITSELF SOMEHOW.
WHAT IF HE FINDS
SOME WAY TO AWAKEN IN THERE?
Researcher #2: THIS CAN'T BE.
WE MUST FIND A WAY
TO DESTROY HIM.
Researcher #3: THE MONSTER
FEEDS ON MASKED VAMPIRES.
HE'S IMMORTAL FOR ALL WE KNOW.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
Researcher #4:
DON'T WORRY, MR. SPEEDWAGON.
HE CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
AS LONG AS HE'S
UNDER THOSE U. V. LIGHTS,
HE WILL REMAIN PETRIFIED
AND CAN POSE NO THREAT TO US.
( researcher #3 laughs )
THAT'S RIGHT.
( researcher #2 laughs )
WELL, I SUPPOSE THAT'S A RELIEF.
Researcher #5: THERE IS STILL
MORE RESEARCH TO BE DONE
IF WE ARE
TO UNDERSTAND HIM FULLY.
♪
( researchers gasp )
Speedwagon: SEE THOSE?
THESE PICTURES
WERE TAKEN IN THE CAVE
WHERE WE ORIGINALLY
FOUND SANTVIENTO.
‐ INSPECT THEM CAREFULLY.
‐ ( researchers gasp )
Researcher #5: THE HORNS.
THEY ALL HAVE
DIFFERENT TYPES OF HORNS.
Researcher #4:
SO IF THE ONE ON THE BOTTOM
IS SUPPOSED TO BE SANTVIENTO,
THEN WHO ARE THE OTHERS?
Speedwagon:
ACCORDING TO VON STROHEIM,
THE GERMANS HAVE UNCOVERED
ANOTHER PILLAR
AT AN UNDISCLOSED LOCATION
SOMEWHERE
ON THE EUROPEAN CONTINENT.
( researchers gasp )
Researcher #2: IS THAT TRUE?
Speedwagon: THEIR FACES
ARE STACKED VERTICALLY
IN THIS PICTURE.
SPEAKING HISTORICALLY,
I WOULD THEORIZE THAT THIS
INDICATES STATUS OR RANK
AMONG THE THREE PILLAR MEN.
JOJO AND I ARE HEADED TO ROME.
VON STROHEIM TOLD HIM
THAT WE MUST GO THERE
IN ORDER TO FIND
THE PERSON WHO CAN HELP US.
AND IT TURNS OUT THAT PERSON...
IS NONE OTHER THAN THE GRANDSON
OF WILL A. ZEPPELI,
CAESAR ZEPPELI.
Caesar: TELL ME,
WHERE MIGHT YOU BE FROM?
WOULD YOU LIKE ME
TO TAKE A PICTURE?
PERHAPS ONE OF YOU
IN THE FOUNTAIN?
Woman: HUH?
( pigeons cooing )
( JoJo imitates cooing )
BOY, THE BIRDS IN THIS COUNTRY
SURE ARE FRIENDLY.
THEY SEEM MUCH SMARTER
THAN THE MEN HERE, TOO.
‐ DON'T YOU THINK?
‐ ( Caesar snorts )
Speedwagon: KNOCK IT OFF, JOJO.
WE DIDN'T COME ALL THIS WAY
FOR NOTHING.
THE TWO OF YOU
BETTER START TALKING.
Caesar: MR. SPEEDWAGON,
I'M SORRY, BUT NOT A CHANCE.
MY GRANDFATHER DIED TRAGICALLY
50 YEARS AGO.
MY FATHER THEN TOOK UP HIS TORCH
AND SPENT HIS LIFE
HUNTING THE MASK.
WE ITALIANS HAVE
THE STRONGEST FAMILIAL BONDS
OF ANY CULTURE IN THE WORLD.
WE ARE VERY PROUD
OF THAT TRADITION.
IT IS EVERYTHING TO US.
THAT'S SOMETHING
HE'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND.
IN FACT, YOU TOLD ME
HE DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT HIS OWN GRANDFATHER
UNTIL JUST RECENTLY.
A TRUE MAN KNOWS HIS HISTORY.
JoJo: TELL ME THIS, TRUE MAN.
IS YOUR WHOLE FAMILY THIS DUMB?
Speedwagon:
THAT'S NOT FAIR, CAESAR.
JOJO DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING,
BECAUSE I KEPT IT ALL
A SECRET FROM HIM.
( Caesar sighs )
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S ANY EXCUSE.
I HEARD ABOUT STRAIZO,
AND I WAS IMPRESSED TO FIND OUT
THAT HE FOUGHT
ONE OF THE PILLAR MEN.
BUT I WANTED TO SEE FOR MYSELF
HOW TOUGH HE WAS,
SO I WAITED AT THE HOTEL.
AND I'M DISAPPOINTED TO SAY
THAT HIS HAMON SKILLS
LEAVE MUCH TO BE DESIRED.
‐ HIS HAMON IS WEAK.
‐ ( JoJo sputtering )
Caesar: IT'S WORTHLESS.
HIS DEFEAT OF THE PILLAR MAN
WAS NOTHING BUT BLIND LUCK!
I WON'T BE FORCED TO WORK
WITH THIS IMBECILE!
Speedwagon: CAESAR,
JUST RELAX FOR A MOMENT.
JOJO IS STILL TRAINING WITH‐‐
( JoJo laughs )
WE'RE DONE
WITH THE NICETIES HERE.
( joints cracking )
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO SETTLE THIS
WITH A GOOD THRASHING.
Caesar: HAMON AS WEAK AS YOURS
COULDN'T PLUCK THE PETALS
OFF THIS DELICATE FLOWER.
( JoJo laughs ) OH, YEAH?
WELL, YOU COULDN'T EVEN
BEAT ONE OF THOSE PIGEONS.
( Caesar chuckles )
( JoJo gasps )
( growls )
ARE YOU GONNA FIGHT ME OR NOT?
IF THERE'S
ANY MOCKING TO BE DONE HERE,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT,
THANK YOU KINDLY.
( gagging )
YOU...BASTARD.
YOU GAVE THIS WOMAN
A HAMON KISS!
Caesar: LIKE I JUST SAID,
YOUR WEAK HAMON COULDN'T
EVEN DEFEAT A WOMAN. SAD.
Speedwagon:
I MUST NOT INTERVENE HERE.
THIS WILL BE
A GOOD LESSON FOR JOJO.
OVERCOMING THIS
WILL ONLY MAKE HIM STRONGER.
( JoJo screams )
( Caesar scoffs )
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
MY GRANDFATHER
MIGHT STILL BE ALIVE
IF YOUR GRANDFATHER
HADN'T GOT IN HIS WAY!
I REFUSE TO ACCEPT YOUR KIND,
YOUR PATHETIC BLOOD.
Speedwagon: THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU'VE CROSSED THE LINE NOW.
JoJo: STOP. I'VE GOT THIS.
SOMEONE AS ARROGANT AS YOU
JUST COULDN'T RESIST
INSULTING MY ENTIRE FAMILY,
COULD YOU?
Caesar: LIKE TO SEE MY MANEUVER
SURE TO ELIMINATE
THE PILLAR MEN?
IT'S A CLEAN TECHNIQUE.
( flowing )
BEHOLD!
MY HAMON BUBBLE LAUNCHER.
( JoJo gasps )
Caesar: IT'S IMPORTANT
TO KEEP ONESELF CLEAN.
I, MYSELF,
HAVE A THIN LAYER OF SOAP
ON MY CLOTHES AT ALL TIMES.
YOU'RE LOOKING A LITTLE DIRTY
YOURSELF THERE, JOESTAR!
JoJo: OHH!
( screams )
( grunting )
( panting )
Caesar: WELL, I AM IMPRESSED
THAT YOU'RE STILL CONSCIOUS,
BUT YOUR WEAK LITTLE HAMON
COULDN'T EVEN POP A BUBBLE.
JUST LOOK AT YOU. YOUR BREATH
IS ALREADY ALL OVER THE PLACE.
ENJOY YOUR STAY, JOESTAR.
JoJo: AND NEXT YOU'LL SAY,
"NOW I'LL LIFT MY HAMON SPELL,
SIGNORINA. THANK YOU."
Caesar: AND NOW
I'LL LIFT MY HAMON SPELL,
SIGNORINA. THANK YOU.
( gagging )
( both panting )
JoJo: WHILE THAT WOMAN
WAS THROTTLING ME,
I FILLED THE PIGEON
WITH AS MUCH HAMON AS I COULD
AND HID IT AWAY IN HER MOUTH.
‐ Caesar: MM?
‐ JoJo: I KNEW YOU'D KISS HER,
EITHER BECAUSE YOU HAD
TO WITHDRAW YOUR HAMON
OR JUST TO SHOW OFF.
SO I WAS RIGHT.
TURNS OUT THAT YOU
COULDN'T EVEN BEAT A PIGEON.
( Caesar scoffs )
( JoJo laughs )
( Speedwagon sighs )
WHAT A DAY.
♪
JoJo: HONESTLY, JUST WHO
DOES THIS JERK THINK HE IS?
GRANDSTANDING LIKE THAT
JUST TO SIT DOWN IN A CHAIR.
I REALLY CAN'T STAND
PEOPLE LIKE HIM.
IF ONLY I HAD A TECHNIQUE
LIKE HIS BUBBLE LAUNCHER.
I'D BE ABLE TO TEACH HIM
SOME HUMILITY THEN.
I HAVE TO GET STRONGER
WITH MY HAMON,
BUT TRAINING
IS ALWAYS SUCH A HASSLE.
HMM. LET'S SEE
HOW OUR LITTLE FRIEND
HANDLES A GAME OF CHANCE.
Caesar: I SAW THAT, JOJO.
DEAL THE CARDS RIGHT.
ONLY COWARDS CHEAT.
JoJo: HUH? WHATEVER DO YOU‐‐
Caesar: DEAL THE CARDS PROPERLY,
JOESTAR, OR PLAY ELSEWHERE.
( JoJo stammers )
FANCY THAT.
WELL, THAT DIDN'T WORK.
( chuckles )
( Caesar scoffs )
PATHETIC.
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED
THAT YOU HAVE TO RESORT
TO CHEATING AND GIMMICKS
TO BEAT ME.
JoJo: YOU REALLY ARE SERIOUS
ABOUT CLEANLINESS.
THIS MIRROR IS SPOTLESS.
Caesar:
STOP PROVOKING ME, JOESTAR!
JoJo: OH,
I HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED!
Speedwagon: CALM DOWN!
IT'S BEEN EIGHT HOURS, CAESAR.
DO YOU MIND TELLING US
WHAT WE'RE WAITING FOR?
( Caesar sighs )
( clock ticking )
JoJo: WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
Caesar: HERE'S YOUR ANSWER.
( JoJo gasps ) WHAT THE HELL
IS A GERMAN SOLDIER DOING HERE?
Caesar: IT LOOKS
LIKE WE'RE CLEAR.
( Speedwagon and JoJo gasp )
Caesar: JUST WHO DO YOU THINK
GUARDS THE PILLAR MEN?
HE'LL GET US IN THERE.
BEHAVE YOURSELF.
JoJo: AGAIN WITH THE GERMANS?
♪
Caesar: GERMANY AND ITALY
HAVE AN ALLIANCE,
AND THE GERMANS ARE INTERESTED
IN RESEARCHING
THE NUANCES OF MY HAMON, SEE?
YOU ENGLISHMEN ARE VERY LUCKY
THAT YOU ARE BEING GRANTED
ACCESS TO VIEW THE PILLAR MEN.
NO NEED TO THANK ME.
YOUR APPRECIATION'S
WRITTEN ON YOUR FACE, JOJO.
‐ Soldier: MR. SPEEDWAGON...
‐ Speedwagon: HUH?
Soldier: WE HAVE
SO MANY QUESTIONS FOR YOU.
I HOPE THAT WE
CAN ALL WORK TOGETHER
TO STOP THE PILLAR MEN
BEFORE THEY AWAKE.
( JoJo scoffs )
Caesar: HOW IS THE BEAUTY?
Soldier: HUH?
Caesar: NOW DON'T BE EMBARRASSED
YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND BACK HOME.
Soldier: WELL. SHE'S‐‐
UH, ACTUALLY, THE TRUTH IS
I'LL BE GOING HOME NEXT WEEK
SO WE CAN FINALLY GET MARRIED.
Caesar: REALLY?
MAMMA MIA!
CONGRATULATIONS, MARK.
I WAS HIS WINGMAN
WHEN HE PICKED HER UP, YOU KNOW.
‐ HE WAS SO NERVOUS.
‐ JoJo: HEARTWARMING.
PLEASE DON'T
GET US ALL KILLED HERE.
AND PLEASE STOP CUDDLING WITH
THE WHEEL, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
Caesar: I WANTED
TO ASK YOU, JOJO,
DO YOU HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND BACK HOME?
( JoJo grumbles )
Caesar: I'LL TAKE THAT AS A NO.
BUT YOU'RE SUCH A GREAT CATCH.
WHY DOESN'T ANYONE
WANT TO DATE YOU?
PERHAPS THEY'RE ALL TOO BUSY
WASHING THEIR HAIR, EH?
( laughing )
JoJo: WHERE DOES
THIS POMPOUS ASS
GET OFF TALKING TO ME LIKE THAT?
ONCE I DEVELOP
MY OWN KILLER TECHNIQUE,
I'LL SHOW HIM A THING OR TWO
OR THREE.
♪
Soldier: LOOK!
THERE'S SOMETHING ON HIS HEAD.
Soldier #2: I DON'T THINK
THAT WAS THERE BEFORE.
Officer: CALM DOWN.
THEY'RE JUST ROCKS
AS LONG AS THEY'RE
UNDER THOSE U. V. LIGHTS.
NO NEED TO WORRY.
NOW GET A CLOSER LOOK!
Soldier #3: YES, SIR.
Officer: THE DEATH
OF VON STROHEIM'S TEAM
IS AN IMPORTANT LESSON
TO US ALL.
ONCE WE CUT THIS PILLAR OUT,
WE'LL HAVE TO SEAL IT
SO THAT IT WILL NEVER SEE
THE LIGHT OF DAY AGAIN.
Soldier #3: I CAN'T TELL
WHAT THAT DARK SPOT IS.
IT LOOKS LIKE A HOLE,
BUT IT MIGHT JUST BE A SHADOW.
Soldier #2: GET A CLOSER LOOK.
Soldier #3: EH?
( wind blows )
D‐DO YOU HEAR THAT?
( gags )
‐ ( soldiers gasp )
‐ Soldier #2: HIS HORN!
Officer: HE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE PETRIFIED!
‐ ( crackling )
‐ HE'S WAKING UP!
QUICKLY!
BRING OUT MORE U. V. LAMPS!
‐ Soldier #4: YES, SIR!
‐ Officer: SCHNELL!
( soldiers gag )
( all gasping )
Officer: THIS CAN'T
BE HAPPENING!
HE'S BLOCKING OUT THE LIGHTS
WITH THE BLOOD OF MY OWN MEN!
♪
( joints crack )
Pillar Man: I SEE THE WORLD
HAS UNDERGONE SIGNIFICANT
CHANGES DURING MY SLUMBER.
THESE INSIGNIFICANT INVENTIONS
MUST BE QUITE POPULAR HERE.
Officer: WHAT'D HE SAY?!
Pillar Man: I SAID
YOUR PITIFUL ILLUMINATIONS
ARE NO MATCH AGAINST MY POWER.
( soldiers scream )
Soldier #4: MY HANDS!
Soldiers: WE'RE STUCK TOGETHER!
( officer gasps )
( yells )
( gasping )
( soldiers groaning )
WAMUU!
NOW IS THE TIME.
AWAKEN, MY MASTERS!
♪
( footsteps echoing )
( JoJo gasps )
Speedwagon: SOMEHOW,
THIS DOESN'T SURPRISE ME.
THE FAMOUS MOUTH OF TRUTH
WAS A SECRET ENTRANCE
ALL THIS TIME.
♪
YOU CAN REALLY FEEL
THE CHILL OF THE DEAD HERE.
CAESAR, WHAT SORT OF EFFECTS
HAS YOUR HAMON HAD
ON THE SLEEPING PILLAR MEN?
Caesar: HAMON IS ONLY USEFUL
ON THE LIVING.
NO REASON TO WASTE
MY POWERS ON STONE.
WE CAN'T LEARN ANYTHING
IF THEY'RE NOT ALIVE.
Speedwagon: HMM.
JoJo: I'M SURPRISED
YOU GERMANS DON'T HAVE
MORE THAN, UH,
ZERO GUARDS DOWN HERE.
IT'S A LITTLE QUIET. HELLO?!
Caesar:
STOP BEING FOOLISH, JOJO.
Mark: WAIT. SOMETHING'S WRONG.
‐ Caesar: HMM?
‐ Mark: HE'S RIGHT.
THERE SHOULD BE GUARDS POSTED
ALL AROUND THIS PLACE.
Caesar: HUH? REALLY?
( JoJo scoffs )
( escaping gas toots )
YAAH!
WHY DIDN'T ANYONE TELL ME
THERE WERE BATS IN HERE?
GROSS. I STEPPED IN BAT DUNG!
AND I JUST CLEANED THESE.
( Mark gasps )
JoJo: WAIT. THOSE ARE...
Caesar: THEY'RE HUSKS
OF DEAD SOLDIERS.
Mark: WHAT‐‐WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED TO THEM?
THEY'RE ALL DEAD! ( screams )
JoJo: STOP WHERE YOU ARE!
WHOEVER DID THIS
COULD STILL BE HERE!
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT'S OUT THERE!
( Mark screams )
JoJo: WHAT‐‐WHAT IS THAT?
Speedwagon: I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY'RE‐‐THEY'RE ALIVE!
Caesar: RUN AWAY, MARK!
GET OUT OF THERE NOW!
NO!
( Mark gasps )
( all gasp )
Caesar: MARK!
( Mark gasping )
Caesar: MARK, NO.
Mark: CAESAR. CAESAR.
Caesar: WHAT HAVE THEY DONE?!
Speedwagon: THEY JUST WALKED
RIGHT THROUGH YOUR FRIEND
LIKE HE WASN'T EVEN THERE.
THE PILLAR MEN HAVE AWOKEN
WITH SUCH MASSIVE POWER
THAT WE BARELY
EVEN EXIST TO THEM.
WE MAY AS WELL BE NOTHING MORE
THAN A COLONY OF ANTS
BENEATH THEIR FEET.
Pillar Man #2: IT APPEARS
TO BE NIGHT OUTSIDE, WAMUU.
Wamuu: THAT IS CORRECT,
LORD KARS.
AND WHAT SHALL BE YOUR BIDDING?
Pillar Man #3: EASY.
WE WILL BE SEARCHING
FOR THE WHEREABOUTS
OF THE RED STONE OF AJA.
THE STONE IS
THE LAST PIECE WE NEED
IN ORDER TO COMPLETE THE MASK.
THEN WE WILL UNLEASH
ITS POWER.
Wamuu: OF COURSE,
MASTER ESIDISI.
HOWEVER, THE HUMAN WORLD
HAS CHANGED MUCH
OVER THE YEARS
THAT WE SLUMBERED.
LONG AGO, IT WAS THE EMPEROR
OF ROME WHO POSSESSED THE STONE.
UNFORTUNATELY, I AM CERTAIN
THAT AGE HAS ENDED.
Kars: WELL, THEN,
WE SIMPLY NEED TO FIND
WHERE IT IS THE STONE
CURRENTLY CALLS HOME.
Wamuu: THEY SAY THE EMPEROR
CHERISHED THE STONE
ABOVE ALL THINGS.
I BELIEVE THAT THE HUMANS OF
TODAY STILL TELL STORIES OF IT.
I SHALL RETRIEVE THE STONE
FOR YOU, MY MASTER.
Kars: THERE'S TIME, WAMUU.
Esidisi: FOR THE MOMENT THEN,
LET US GO OUTSIDE
AND OBSERVE THE CHANGES
THAT HAVE OCCURRED
IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
Kars: HMM.
( Wamuu grunts )
‐ ( gasps )
‐ Esidisi: WAMUU!
EXPLAIN YOUR INSOLENCE.
Kars: STAY YOUR HAND, ESIDISI.
Wamuu: I APOLOGIZE, LORD KARS.
Kars: OF COURSE.
IT HAD SLIPPED MY MIND
THAT YOU POSSESS
A REFLEXIVE ATTACK
AGAINST ANYONE
WHO DARES TO WALK
ACROSS THE DEPTHS
OF YOUR SHADOW.
IT HAS BEEN 2,000 YEARS,
AFTER ALL.
Wamuu: I HAVE OFFENDED YOU,
MY LORD.
I WILL ACCEPT
WHATEVER PUNISHMENT YOU SEE FIT.
( Kars chuckles )
I SIMPLY CANNOT ACCEPT
YOUR APOLOGY.
YOUR INNATE FIGHTING SPIRIT
IS WHAT MAKES YOU
A GREAT WARRIOR,
AND THAT IS WHY I TRUST YOU.
THE FAULT IS MY OWN
FOR TREADING UPON YOUR DARKNESS.
PLEASE FORGIVE MY TRANSGRESSION.
Wamuu: YOU ARE TOO KIND.
( Kars chuckles )
RISE, WAMUU.
Wamuu: YES, MASTER.
( Mark groaning ) CAESAR!
KILL ME, PLEASE. DO IT.
YOU'VE GOT TO KILL ME NOW.
Caesar: I CAN'T.
Mark: IT'S‐‐
IT'S GETTING SO COLD.
PLEASE, CAESAR.
I'M‐‐I'M SO SCARED.
I COULDN'T FEEL ANYTHING
AT FIRST,
BUT NOW, THE PAIN.
PLEASE, CAESAR,
YOU'VE GOT TO KILL ME NOW.
Caesar: MARK.
( JoJo thinking )
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
TO HELP THIS POOR BASTARD.
I FEEL SO POWERLESS.
I MUST CONTROL MYSELF.
I FEEL LIKE
I'M GOING TO EXPLODE.
♪
‐ ( gasps )
‐ ( Speedwagon gasps )
GOODBYE, FRIEND.
( Caesar breathes deeply )
Speedwagon: CAESAR.
( Mark sighs )
GIVE HER MY LOVE, CAESAR.
( Caesar gasps )
( crying )
I PROMISE.
♪
HE WAS SO YOUNG,
HIS WHOLE LIFE AHEAD OF HIM.
HE WORKED HARD FOR A LIVING.
HE LOVED HIS FAMILY DEARLY.
HE LOVED HIS GIRL
AND HIS COUNTRY.
HE WAS A GOOD PERSON,
CLEAN‐CUT, THE BOY NEXT DOOR.
AND THEY KILLED HIM.
NOW THEY DIE!
JoJo: CAESAR!
Caesar: DON'T YOU DARE
GET IN MY WAY, JOJO.
I'M GOING TO ENJOY
EVERY SECOND OF THIS!
THIS IS PERSONAL.
I'LL DESTROY
THESE FIENDS MYSELF!
♪
♪ ALONG THE DRIFTING CLOUD
♪ THE EAGLE SEARCHING DOWN
ON THE LAND ♪
♪ CATCHING THE SWIRLING WIND
♪ THE SAILOR SEES THE RIM
OF THE LAND ♪
♪ THE EAGLE'S DANCING WINGS
♪ CREATE AS WEATHER
SPINS OUT OF HAND ♪
♪ GO CLOSER, HOLD THE LAND
♪ FEEL PARTLY
NO MORE THAN GRAINS OF SAND ♪
♪ WE STAND TO LOSE ALL TIME
♪ A THOUSAND ANSWERS BY
IN OUR HAND ♪
♪ NEXT TO YOUR DEEPER FEARS
♪ WE STAND SURROUNDED
BY A MILLION YEARS ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS WILL MAKE YOU
OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS WILL MAKE YOU
OUT AND OUT ♪
♪
JoJo: OH, I'M SICK AND TIRED
OF ALL THIS TALKING.
Wamuu: EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO GET AT?
Caesar: I KNEW HE WAS SPINELESS.
Kars: THESE HUMANS KNOW HAMON.
Wamuu: I CALL THAT
DIVINE SANDSTORM.