Narrator: WITH THE HELP
OF CAESAR'S BANDANA,
JOJO BARELY MANAGED
TO DEFEAT WAMUU.
THEN IT WAS KARS'S TURN
TO FACE LISA LISA
IN THEIR ONE‐ON‐ONE COMBAT.
♪
SUDDENLY VON STROHEIM SHOWED UP
TO BATTLE THE VAMPIRES,
ALONG WITH SPEEDWAGON
AND SMOKEY.
IN A COWARDLY TURN, KARS USED
A DOUBLE TO DECEIVE LISA LISA.
THEN HE LITERALLY
STABBED HER IN THE BACK
TO USE AS A PAWN AGAINST JOJO.
JOJO AND LISA LISA
ARE IN THE GREATEST PERIL
OF THEIR LIVES.
( JoJo yells )
KARS, YOU BASTARD!
THERE'S A PLACE
WAITING FOR YOU IN HELL!
Smokey: JOJO DOESN'T KNOW.
HE DOESN'T KNOW THE WOMAN
HE'S TRYING TO SAVE
IS HIS MOTHER.
( men's chorus singing )
( JoJo grunts )
Kars: YOU DON'T WANT
TO LET GO OF THAT, JOJO.
IT'S A FOREST
OF CRYSTAL SPIKES DOWN THERE.
SHE WOULD DIE HORRIBLY.
JoJo: KARS!
YOU HAVE LIVED FOR FAR TOO LONG.
YOUR SOUL'S DECAYED.
IT'S LIKE A PUMPKIN LEFT TO ROT
OUT IN A DEAD FIELD.
EVEN FLIES AVOID IT.
Kars: YES, GRUMBLE AT ME.
SHOUT YOUR LUNGS OUT.
HEAVE YOUR INSULTS AT ME,
FOR AS LONG AS YOU'RE
HOLDING ON TO THAT ROPE,
MY FRIEND,
THAT'S ABOUT ALL YOU CAN DO.
( JoJo growls )
( chorus continues )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( JoJo grunting )
‐ ( JoJo groans )
‐ ( both gasp )
( JoJo panting )
Speedwagon: JOJO! LISA LISA!
Smokey: HE CAN'T FOLLOW
WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON.
HE DOESN'T REALIZE
THAT'S HIS MOTHER HE'S HOLDING.
MR. SPEEDWAGON,
WE NEED TO TELL JOJO.
Speedwagon: NOT YET.
Smokey: BUT WHY NOT?!
Speedwagon: IT'S NOT
THE PROPER TIME.
VON STROHEIM!
HAVE YOU FINISHED DISPOSING
OF THOSE VAMPIRES YET?!
WE MUST HELP JOJO.
‐ Von Stroheim: JA, RIGHT.
‐ ( vampires yell )
Von Stroheim: YOU THINK
I JUST HAVE TO WAVE
MY MAGIC FLASHLIGHT
UND THEN IT'S ALL DONE?!
( vampires screaming )
Von Stroheim: OUT OF SIGHT
UND OUT OF MIND!
( growling )
( vampires growling )
Speedwagon: VON STROHEIM HAS
GOT HIS HANDS FULL RIGHT NOW.
Smokey: JOJO.
Kars: CAREFUL NOW.
THAT ROPE LOOKS LIKE
IT'S STARTING TO SLIP A LITTLE.
( JoJo grunts )
‐ ( growls )
‐ Kars: HMM?
( JoJo yells )
Kars: AS LONG
AS YOU'RE HOLDING ON
SO TIGHTLY TO THAT ROPE,
YOUR CLUMSY FEET
HAVE LIMITED REACH.
‐ ( yells )
‐ ( JoJo screaming )
Speedwagon: OH, NO.
HIS KICK DID MAKE IT TO KARS,
BUT THERE WAS NO HAMON.
( Smokey gasps )
WE'RE IN REAL TROUBLE.
Kars: YOU POOR BOY,
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
RUNNING OUT OF HAMON.
BUT IT IS POSSIBLE
YOU MIGHT HAVE ENOUGH LEFT
TO MAKE
ONE LAST‐DITCH ATTACK ON ME.
( JoJo growls )
Kars: I'LL WALK UP THERE,
AND THEN I'M GOING
TO TAKE YOUR LIFE AS EASILY
AS IF I WERE PLUCKING A LITTLE
FLOWER ALONG A GARDEN PATHWAY.
( JoJo spits )
‐ KARS.
‐ Kars: MMM?
JoJo: MAYBE THERE
IS ENOUGH LEFT IN ME,
ENOUGH HAMON
FOR ONE LAST DESPERATE ATTACK.
TO BE HONEST, EVEN I DON'T KNOW.
Kars: HMM?
JoJo: BUT EITHER WAY,
I'VE DEVISED A CUNNING PLAN.
I GUARANTEE IT'S SOMETHING
TO MAKE YOU CHOKE.
HOW BADLY DO YOU
WANT TO KNOW WHAT IT IS?
'CAUSE I'M NOT TELLING!
Kars: HEY.
I CAN SEE THAT YOU'VE STOPPED
TYING THOSE ROPES TOGETHER NOW.
HMM?
JoJo: YOU SEE THIS MATCH?
WHAT DO YOU THINK I'M GOING
TO BE DOING WITH THIS FIRE?
Kars: HUMPH.
Smokey: HUH?
WHAT ON EARTH IS JOJO THINKING?
HE SET HIS SCARF ON FIRE.
JoJo: BEFORE THIS FLAME
HAS A CHANCE TO BURN ME,
I'M GOING TO FIND A WAY
TO USE WHATEVER I CAN
TO SEND YOU STRAIGHT TO HELL.
THE SCARF IS A GAMBLE,
SOMETHING TO MOTIVATE ME,
A LITTLE PAIN
TO HELP ME FIND A WAY.
Kars: JOJO, COME ON NOW.
YOU CAN'T FOOL ME.
THAT'S JUST
AN ACT OF DESPERATION!
♪
DON'T TOY WITH ME.
YOU'RE JUST DODGING AROUND
FOR A CHANCE
TO CATCH YOUR BREATH.
IT'S NO MATTER.
I'M TAKING YOUR LIFE
AT THE MOMENT OF MY CHOICE,
I'M TIRED OF DEALING
WITH YOUR SILLY ANTICS.
JoJo: OH, COME ON.
I NEED TO BREATHE.
SO WHAT IF I
LOOK SILLY DOING IT?
JOJO, LOOK.
CLEARLY I CAN SEVER
LISA LISA'S ROPE
WITH JUST A FLICK OF MY WRIST,
AND IF YOU DODGE ME AGAIN,
THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT I WILL DO.
( JoJo groans )
Kars: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD I PRESS
JUST A LITTLE HARDER?
( chuckles )
IT'S SO EASY.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
JoJo: DON'T DO IT!
Kars: YOU RAN AWAY BEFORE.
NOW COME TOWARD ME SLOWLY.
HEH. OR YOU COULD
STAY WHERE YOU ARE
AND WATCH AS I
CUT THROUGH THE LINE.
‐ ( JoJo growls )
‐ Speedwagon: THE COWARD.
Kars: SO, WHAT THEN?
IS YOUR LIFE MORE PRECIOUS
THAN THAT OF THE WOMAN
DANGLING DOWN THERE?
( JoJo growls )
HAH!
( yells ) HERE'S MY CHOICE!
Kars: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING,
BUT WHEN I CUT THIS LINE,
YOU WILL BOTH BE IMPALED
ON THE CRYSTAL SPIKES BELOW.
YOU FOOL!
Smokey: JOJO!
Speedwagon: LISA LISA!
Kars: HEH. IDIOT.
TWO BIRDS WITH ONE CUT.
‐ ( JoJo grunts )
‐ Kars: HUH?
WHAT?! BUT HE‐‐
THIS ROPE,
IT'S CONNECTED TO JOJO.
( both gasp )
Kars: WHEN DID HE
MAKE THIS HAPPEN?
HE DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH TIME TO‐‐
OH. WHEN HE FIRST KICKED AT ME,
HE ALLOWED HIMSELF TO BE CUT
ALONG WITH THE ROPE.
AND THEN WHEN HE IGNITED
THAT DAMNED MATCH,
HE SECRETLY TIED HIS LEG
TO THE ROPE ON LISA LISA.
I SEE IT NOW.
HE NEEDED
SOME KIND OF DISTRACTION.
THAT'S WHEN HE SET
HIS SCARF ON FIRE.
( no audible dialogue )
AND THEN TO TIE
THE LINES TOGETHER,
HE MANEUVERED ME
INTO DOING HIS WORK FOR HIM
BY CUTTING LISA LISA'S ROPE.
THAT MANIPULATING CHEAT.
JoJo: NOW YOU'RE THE ONE
SAVING BOTH ME AND LISA LISA.
Kars: YOU DECEIVED ME, JOJO!
JoJo: HOW ODD THAT I SHOULD HEAR
YOU COMPLAINING ABOUT TRICKERY.
YOU ENJOY DECEIVING OTHERS,
BUT NOW THE SHOE'S
ON THE OTHER FOOT.
YOU MAY HAVE LIVED
FOR OVER 10,000 YEARS,
BUT IF YOU'RE GOING UP
AGAINST MY SKILLS,
YOU NEED ANOTHER DECADE!
YOU'RE THROUGH!
( Kars screams )
( JoJo yells )
HAMON OVERDRIVE!
( panting )
DID IT WORK?
THAT WAS THE LAST OF MY HAMON.
I'M BURNED OUT.
I DON'T HAVE
AN OUNCE OF STRENGTH LEFT.
( Kars shuddering )
( screams )
JoJo: YES. IT WAS ENOUGH.
Speedwagon: OH, YES!
Smokey: HE DID IT.
HE HIT KARS WITH HIS HAMON.
( Kars groaning )
JoJo: OFF YOU GO.
I'LL GET YOU.
( men's boots shuffling )
Von Stroheim: OHH!
LOOK AT THAT.
KARS FELL RIGHT
ONTO HIS OWN CRYSTAL SPIKES.
‐ ( men's chorus singing )
‐ ( Kars groaning )
Von Stroheim: BWA HA HA HA!
THE PILLAR MAN IS DONE!
SEE?! THE HAMON WILL TRAVEL
RIGHT UP HIS ARM UND DO THE JOB!
YOU'RE WEAK!
YOUR TIME ON EARTH IS UP!
A MERE HUMAN
COULD FINISH YOU OFF NOW!
( men yelling )
♪
( men gasp )
( sizzling )
Von Stroheim: OHH.
TRYING TO SPOOK US, EH?
NOW LET'S ELIMINATE HIM FOREVER.
BRING OUT
THE ULTRAVIOLET AMPLIFIER.
Germans: JAWOHL!
( Lisa Lisa panting )
JoJo: LISA LISA.
( panting )
KARS SAID THAT HE
WASN'T ACTUALLY PLANNING
TO KILL YOU WITH HIS BLADE,
SO I DON'T THINK
THAT YOUR WOUNDS ARE FATAL.
WE NEED TO GET YOU
TAKEN CARE OF QUICKLY,
BUT I DON'T THINK THIS IS
THE DAY YOU'RE GOING TO DIE.
♪
( Smokey sighs )
IT'S FINALLY DONE.
Speedwagon: LOOKS LIKE IT,
AND I'M GLAD.
Smokey: SAY, MR. SPEEDWAGON,
‐ UM...
‐ Speedwagon: HUH?
Smokey: CAN I PLEASE
ASK YOU SOMETHING?
Speedwagon: OF COURSE.
Smokey: WELL, WHY DID
GRANNY ERINA LIE TO JOJO?
WHY'D SHE TELL HIM
THAT HIS MOTHER
HAD DIED WHEN HE WAS LITTLE BOY?
WHY DOES LISA LISA HIDE HER PAST
AND NOT TELL HIM
WHO SHE REALLY IS?
Speedwagon: SMOKEY, THAT'S, UH‐‐
Smokey: I KNOW GRANNY ERINA
TOLD ME NOT TO ASK YOU,
BUT I'VE GOTTA FIGURE THIS OUT.
I MEAN, SHE IS HIS MOTHER.
KEEPING THAT INFORMATION
FROM HIM IS JUST AWFUL.
Speedwagon: SMOKEY.
Smokey: JOJO AND GRANNY ERINA,
THEY'RE MY FRIENDS.
BACK IN NEW YORK,
THEY BOTH SAVED ME.
I WAS JUST A LOWLY PICKPOCKET,
BUT THEY HELPED ME OUT ANYWAY.
THAT'S THE REASON I'M HERE.
I'M GOING TO DO
ANYTHING I CAN TO HELP.
♪
( Speedwagon sighs )
ALL RIGHT THEN, SMOKEY.
LET ME TELL YOU.
IN NEW YORK, YOU PROVED
WHAT A GOOD FRIEND YOU WERE.
YOU TOOK EXCELLENT CARE OF ERINA
WHILE I WAS GONE.
BUT THIS, YOU CAN
NEVER REVEAL TO JOJO.
THIS IS THE BUSINESS
OF THE JOESTAR FAMILY.
FRIENDS OR NOT, WE DON'T HAVE
THE RIGHT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
THE NAME LISA LISA
IS MADE UP, AN ALIAS.
HER REAL GIVEN NAME
IS ELIZABETH.
RAISED AND TRAINED
BY THE HAMON‐USER STRAIZO
YOU MET...
SHE AND ERINA'S SON,
GEORGE JOESTAR, FELL IN LOVE.
THEY GOT MARRIED.
( baby JoJo crying )
Speedwagon: SOON GEORGE
AND ELIZABETH HAD A SON.
YOU KNOW HIM AS JOJO.
JOJO'S FATHER, GEORGE, ENLISTED
AS A MEMBER OF BRITAIN'S
ROYAL FLYING CORPS.
AVIATION DEVELOPED RAPIDLY
DURING THE FIRST WORLD WAR,
AND GEORGE WAS AMONG
THE BRAVE PILOTS
TO FLY INTO BATTLE IN THE SKIES.
HE STOOD OUT AS A HERO,
EVEN AMONG THE MEMBERS
OF THE ROYAL FLYING CORPS.
IT WAS THEN...
♪
THAT A GUT‐WRENCHING HORROR
FROM THE PAST
CAME BACK TO HAUNT THE MEMBERS
OF THE JOESTAR FAMILY.
50 YEARS EARLIER,
DIO BRANDO CREATED
BLOODSUCKING ZOMBIES.
STRAIZO, MYSELF, AND THE OTHERS
BELIEVED THAT WE
HAD EXTERMINATED THEM.
BUT ONE OF THEM HAD ESCAPED.
HE HID HIMSELF WITHIN SOCIETY
AND LIVED FOR DECADES
UNDISCOVERED.
HE WAS CUNNING, INTELLIGENT,
SUPREMELY DANGEROUS.
( zombie growls )
Speedwagon: HE CREATED NO SPAWN.
HE DEVOURED THE BONES
AND HAIR OF HIS VICTIMS,
LEAVING BEHIND
NO EVIDENCE OF HIS EXISTENCE.
( bones crunching )
Speedwagon:
AND BY SOME WRETCHED,
WICKED TWIST OF FATE...
HE HAD PLACED HIMSELF
IN POSITION
AS A COMMANDER
IN THE ROYAL FLYING CORPS.
Smokey: THE ROYAL FLYING CORPS?
WITH JOJO'S FATHER?
Speedwagon: THE VERY SAME.
GEORGE WAS OBSERVANT
AND FIGURED THIS OUT.
HE HAD LISTENED WELL
TO STRAIZO AND MYSELF.
BUT ULTIMATELY, GEORGE WAS
ONLY AN ORDINARY MAN.
HE HAD CHARACTER AND TALENT,
BUT HE HAD NO TRAINING
IN THE WAYS OF HAMON.
( George gasps )
Speedwagon: BEFORE HE WAS ABLE
TO UNMASK THE COMMANDER,
HE WAS DISCOVERED
BY HIS MONSTROUS QUARRY.
HIS MESSAGE TO STRAIZO
WAS TOO LATE.
( George gags )
♪
Speedwagon: GEORGE'S DEATH
WAS COVERED UP
AS AN UNFORTUNATE
NIGHTTIME PLANE CRASH.
STRAIZO AND I
FOUND THIS SUSPICIOUS,
SO WE INVESTIGATED AND
EVENTUALLY LEARNED THE TRUTH.
THAT NIGHT,
ELIZABETH HELD AN INFANT JOJO
AS I TOLD HER
WHAT WE HAD DISCOVERED.
INSTEAD OF SHOWING GRIEF,
SHE RAN OUT
INTENT ON BLOODY REVENGE.
( zombie gasps )
( screams )
Speedwagon: SHE WAS
A GENIUS WITH HAMON,
BUT SHE LET HER EMOTIONS
CONSUME HER.
SHE WAS CARELESS.
THERE WAS A WITNESS
TO THE COMMANDER'S DEATH.
( soldier screams )
( running footsteps )
Speedwagon: THE MILITARY KNEW
NOTHING ABOUT ZOMBIES OR HAMON.
THEY CONCLUDED
THAT FOR SOME UNKNOWN REASON,
ELIZABETH HAD ATTACKED
THEIR BELOVED COMMANDER,
KILLED HIM, THEN BURNED HIS BODY
TO HIDE THE CRIME.
WORD SPREAD
AS ONLY BAD NEWS CAN,
AND SOON SHE WAS KNOWN
AROUND THE WORLD AS A MURDERER
AND TRAITOR TO THE WAR EFFORT.
( running footsteps )
♪
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
Speedwagon:
WE USED ALL THE RESOURCES
OF THE SPEEDWAGON FOUNDATION
TO COVER HER TRAIL.
ELIZABETH HAD TO LEAVE
ENGLAND BEHIND
WITHOUT EVEN A WORD
OF GOODBYE TO HER SON.
( JoJo crying )
Speedwagon: ERINA KNEW
WHAT HAD OCCURRED,
AND SHE GAVE ME
THIS SPECIFIC REQUEST.
Erina: WHEN THE CHILD GROWS UP
AND ASKS ABOUT HIS PARENTS,
PLEASE TELL HIM
THEY BOTH DIED IN THE WAR.
( Speedwagon gasps )
( sighs )
Erina: THIS CHILD,
POOR LITTLE CHILD.
Speedwagon: AND SO IT WAS
THAT ELIZABETH BECAME LISA LISA.
Smokey: WHY?
WHY IS IT THAT WAY?
AT LEAST LET HIM KNOW
HIS MOTHER'S NOT DEAD SOMEWHERE!
Speedwagon: I KNOW
PAINFULLY WELL WHY.
ERINA LOST HER HUSBAND
AND HER SON
IN THE BATTLE BETWEEN HAMON
AND THE STONE MASKS.
BUT THINKING OF HER GRANDSON,
HER JOSEPH, HER JOJO,
SHE DIDN'T WANT HAMON TO CREATE
YET ANOTHER HOLE IN HER LIFE!
LISA LISA FEELS THE SAME.
( Smokey gasps )
♪
WHAT TRAGEDY FOR THIS FAMILY.
SUCH A MISERABLE FORTUNE.
BUT NOW...
IT'S BETTER.
JOJO USED HAMON POSITIVELY
TO SAVE HIS MOTHER'S LIFE.
MR. SPEEDWAGON.
Speedwagon: HMM?
Smokey: THERE'S NO REASON
FOR LISA LISA
TO HIDE THE TRUTH
FROM JOJO ANY LONGER.
Speedwagon: EH?
Smokey: HE ALREADY
KNOWS ABOUT HAMON,
AND HE USED IT
TO SAVE HIS MOTHER'S LIFE.
Speedwagon: THAT'S TRUE.
BUT STILL IT'S NOT
MY DECISION TO MAKE.
IT'S A QUESTION OF HOW ERINA
AND LISA LISA FEEL.
Smokey: I GUESS.
German: MAJOR!
WE'RE READY TO FIRE, SIR.
Von Stroheim: EXCELLENT.
EVERYONE FOCUS ON HIM.
UND NOW WE WILL SHARE
THE HONOR OF EXECUTING KARS.
Germans: JAWOHL!
( men's chorus singing )
( laughs ) NOW, KARS, DIE!
I CAN'T BEGIN TO TELL YOU
HOW GOOD IT FEELS
TO GIVE THIS ORDER MYSELF!
( chorus continues )
( all yell, gasp )
Speedwagon: VON STROHEIM,
YOU MUST STOP!
HE'S GOT THE RED STONE ATTACHED
RIGHT THERE ON HIS MASK!
U.V. LIGHT WILL HELP HIM!
Von Stroheim: NO, DAMN IT.
STOP NOW!
DON'T FIRE THE U. V. AMPLIFIER!
THIS CAN'T BE!
( woman vocalizing )
♪
( Von Stroheim stammering )
I DIDN'T SEE HIM WITH THE MASK.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT HE HAD IT
ANYWHERE NEAR HIM.
I DIDN'T SEE HIM
PUT IN THE RED STONE.
Speedwagon: NO, IT CAN'T BE.
DEAR GOD.
JoJo: KARS.
( woman vocalizing )
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ WITH YOU
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
( vocalizing )
♪
Von Stroheim:
HE HAS BECOME THE UBERMENSCH.
Speedwagon: HE HAS COMPLETE
MASTERY OVER ORGANIC LIFE.
Smokey: IS THERE REALLY NO WAY
TO STOP HIM, MR. SPEEDWAGON?
Speedwagon:
KARS THE PILLAR MAN IS NO MORE.
HE'S BECOME KARS,
THE ULTIMATE CREATION!