( Dio screams )
THE HAMON...
HAS ALMOST REACHED
MY HEAD AND BRAIN.
MUST DO SOMETHING.
MOVE, ARM. MOVE!
( gags )
♪
Apothecary: OHH. ( gasping )
LORD DIO.
WE'LL GET A NEW BODY FOR YOU.
Narrator: EXCERPT FROM
THE DECEMBER 4, 1888, EDITION
OF THE "LONDON PRESS:"
"IT HAS BEEN REPORTED
THAT 73 OF THE 452 RESIDENTS
"IN THE TOWN
OF WIND KNIGHTS LOT
"HAVE GONE MISSING OVERNIGHT.
"THE POLICE HAVE BEEN
PURSUING LINES OF INQUIRY
"BASED ON CERTAIN
WITNESS ACCOUNTS.
"THESE ACCOUNTS STATE
THAT FOUR OUTSIDERS
"WERE SEEN BURNING
A MAN'S CLOTHING
"AT THE BASE OF A NEARBY CLIFF.
"ONE OF THE FOUR WAS REPORTEDLY
WIELDING A LARGE HAMMER
AND USING IT TO SMASH
A CURIOUS STONE MASK."
Speedwagon:
OUR WORK HERE IS DONE.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( bells pealing )
Speedwagon:
"HEIR TO THE JOESTAR FORTUNE,
"JONATHAN JOESTAR WEDS ERINA,
"ONLY DAUGHTER
OF THE PENDLETONS.
THE COUPLE WILL TRAVEL
TO THE AMERICAS."
NICE.
( gasps )
BLAZES!
LOOK WHAT TIME IT IS!
THEIR SHIP'S ABOUT TO LEAVE!
♪
OI!
Poco: EH? MR. SPEEDWAGON!
YOU ALMOST MISSED
BEING ABLE TO SAY GOODBYE.
Speedwagon: SORRY I'M SO LATE.
SO THEN, WHERE ARE THEY?
Poco: THEY'RE BOTH
ONBOARD THE SHIP.
Speedwagon: EH?!
Poco: IT'S ABOUT READY TO SAIL.
Speedwagon: WHAT? IT IS?
WHERE ARE THEY?
I'VE GOT TO SEE THEM.
Priest: NOW THEN, FATHER STYX,
WE EXPECT TO HEAR GREAT THINGS
FROM YOUR MISSION TO MEXICO.
Styx: I'LL CERTAINLY
DO WHAT I CAN.
Speedwagon: JONATHAN JOESTAR!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
Longshoreman:
WATCH WHERE YOU'RE GOIN'!
WHAT MAKES THIS THING
SO BLASTED HEAVY, ANYWAY?
Longshoreman #2:
HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
WE BEEN HIRED
BY THAT ASIAN BLOKE,
SO WE MOVE IT WHERE HE SAYS.
‐ ( thumping )
‐ Longshoreman #1: HMM?
‐ ( deep breath )
( gasps )
OI. DID‐‐DID YOU BOYS
HEAR THAT?
Longshoreman #2: QUIT FLAPPIN'
YOUR BLASTED CAKE HOLE.
‐ ( bell ringing )
‐ NOW MOVE IT!
WE DON'T GET PAID
'TIL THIS JOB'S DONE.
( ringing continue )
Speedwagon: OW. RUDDY HOOLIGANS.
‐ Poco: MR. SPEEDWAGON.
‐ Speedwagon: HMM?
Poco: LOOK. THEY'RE UP THERE.
HELLO!
JONATHAN!
♪
Speedwagon:
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL SIGHT.
I WISH YOU
A LONG, LOVE‐FILLED LIFE.
I'LL ALWAYS BE HERE FOR YOU.
IF YOU EVER NEED ME,
JUST CALL. I'LL BE THERE.
THOUGH AT THE MOMENT,
I'D JUST BE IN THE WAY, EH?
( ship's horn blows )
‐ Crowd: BYE!
‐ ( Poco laughs )
‐ Poco: BON VOYAGE!
HAVE A WONDERFUL TRIP!
♪
( Erina gasps )
( bird chirps )
POOR LITTLE BIRD, ALL ALONE.
DID YOU LOSE YOUR FLOCK?
( wings flap )
JoJo: ERINA.
SOMETHING WRONG, LOVE?
DEAR, WHAT ARE YOU
CRYING ABOUT?
Erina: THESE TEARS
THAT I'M CRYING ARE FROM JOY,
JOY THAT I AM HERE WITH YOU.
EVEN AS A BOY, YOU STROVE
TO BE A TRUE GENTLEMAN,
A CHAMPION OF OTHERS, NO MATTER
THE CONSEQUENCE TO YOURSELF.
AND NOW THAT PROUD AND NOBLE
JONATHAN JOESTAR
IS HERE IN MY ARMS.
JoJo: AND I HAVE YOU.
WHEN MY HEART
WAS FROZEN IN DESPAIR,
YOU WARMED ME
AND BROUGHT ME BACK TO LIFE.
I AM FORTUNATE
TO HAVE SAVED A WORLD
THAT HAS YOU IN IT.
I ONLY WISH FATHER
COULD HAVE KNOWN YOU.
ERINA, COME. SUPPER IS WAITING.
‐ Erina: JONATHAN!
‐ ( JoJo grunts )
( groaning )
Erina: UM, I WANTED
TO TELL YOU TO BE CAREFUL
SO YOU WOULDN'T BASH YOUR HEAD.
( both laughing )
Erina: AH, I WISH THAT TODAY
WOULD LAST FOREVER.
( wind blowing )
Styx: DAMN, IT FELL
INTO THE ENGINE ROOM.
THAT'S A FILTHY PLACE
TO GO AFTER IT.
( hiccups )
I COULD JUST SELL IT,
BUT IT BRINGS IN THE SHEKELS.
( groans )
DEAR LORD.
YOU SURELY DO SEEM
TO ENJOY PICKING ON ME.
♪
Erina: OH. NO.
I HAVEN'T THE EXPERIENCE
DRINKING A MAN DOES.
JoJo: JUST A BIT,
BARELY ENOUGH TO GET THE TASTE.
IT REALLY ISN'T STRONG AT ALL.
I THINK IT'S GOOD.
HERE.
( chuckles )
( Erina sighs )
JoJo: EH?
( gasps )
NO. IT CAN'T BE.
♪
( Erina gasps ) JONATHAN?
( JoJo gasps )
IMPOSSIBLE.
THERE IS NO WAY.
HE'S HERE. DIO'S ALIVE.
( apothecary chuckles )
JoJo: ERINA, GO.
BACK TO OUR CABIN NOW.
AND DON'T FORGET
TO LOCK THE DOOR.
( Erina sighs )
♪
Styx: HUMPH.
EH?
WELL, THAT'S RATHER STRANGE.
THE LOCK'S UNDONE.
QUEER BIT OF BUSINESS.
I CAN SEE A METAL CATCH
GLINTING ON THE INSIDE THERE.
BUT THAT WOULD MEAN...
THAT THIS TRUNK
IS LOCKED FROM THE INSIDE!
( gags )
JoJo: HALT!
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE!
Dio: WHERE IS...
MY BODY?
JoJo: D‐DIO.
Erina: JONATHAN IS SO UPSET.
SOMETHING IS WRONG.
‐ ( zombie growls )
‐ ( woman yelps )
Dio: JOJO.
DO YOU SEE THE CONDITION
IN WHICH I FIND MYSELF?
YOUR WORK.
THERE IS A REASON I
DISPLAY MYSELF TO YOU LIKE THIS.
( JoJo gasps )
Dio: WHY WOULD
I SHOW MY WEAKNESS
TO MY DEADLIEST FOE?
BECAUSE THOUGH
I ONCE DESPISED YOU,
NOW I HAVE ONLY
THE GREATEST RESPECT
FOR YOUR SPIRIT,
YOUR VALOR IN BATTLE,
YOUR POWER.
I SEE IT NOW,
HOW INCREDIBLE YOU ARE.
JoJo: DIO.
Dio: JOJO.
IF NOT FOR YOU,
I WOULD NEVER HAVE OBTAINED
THE POWER OF THE STONE MASK.
HOWEVER, YOUR DAMNABLE MEDDLING
COST ME WORLD DOMINATION.
IF THERE REALLY IS A GOD,
ONE WHO PLUCKS
THE STRINGS OF OUR FATE,
I AM CERTAIN THAT OUR FATES WERE
BOUND TOGETHER FOR A REASON.
OUR TWO EXISTENCES WERE ONLY
EVER INTENDED TO BE BUT ONE,
AND SO I WILL TAKE THE BODY
OF THE ONLY MAN ON EARTH
I RESPECT.
THEN I WILL LIVE
IN ETERNAL GLORY,
FOR THAT IS THE DESTINY
WHICH IS WAITING FOR ME.
THERE WILL BE NO PAIN.
THAT IS THE FINAL GIFT
I BEQUEATH TO YOU.
( JoJo gasps ) NO.
NO, THOSE EYES. I CAN'T...
Dio: LIVE ON AS MY BODY, JOJO!
( JoJo gasps )
Erina: JONATHAN! WHAT‐‐
ERINA.
( ship's horn blows )
( beams strike )
( JoJo gasps )
( gags )
Erina: NO. JONATHAN.
JoJo: ERI...NA.
Dio: OH...
A PITY YOU WOULDN'T HEAR ME.
IF ONLY YOU HAD REMAINED STILL
AS I TOLD YOU,
YOUR DEATH IN FACT
WOULD HAVE BEEN QUITE PAINLESS.
TORN FROM YOUR
LITTLE FAIRY TALE INTO HELL,
THRUST INTO A REALITY
YOU DIDN'T KNOW EXISTED,
WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
DID JOJO NEVER TELL YOU OF ME,
THE EVIL THAT DWELLS THERE
IN THE DARKNESS?
I MAY NOT LOOK
LIKE MUCH RIGHT NOW,
BUT SURELY YOU REMEMBER ME,
ERINA PENDLETON.
WAIT.
IT'S ERINA JOESTAR NOW,
ISN'T IT?
Erina: DIO!
( zombies growling )
( man screams )
THE SHIP'S FULL OF MONSTERS!
‐ ( woman screams )
‐ Man: RUN!
( zombie growling )
( woman gasping )
♪
( Erina gasps )
( baby crying )
( apothecary laughs )
AS YOU ORDERED, LORD, I DRAINED
THE LIFE OF ONLY ONE PASSENGER,
AND NOW MOST OF THE SHIP
HAS JOINED OUR LITTLE FAMILY.
( laughs )
AND NOW WE WILL PROCEED
TO AMERICA.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, LORD DIO?
JoJo: I CAN'T SPEAK.
I CAN'T EVEN TAKE A BREATH.
I HAVE TO MOVE.
ERINA. ERINA.
( gags )
I HAVE TO SAVE‐‐
( yelps )
( apothecary chuckles )
( JoJo gasps )
CAN'T GATHER HAMON.
( apothecary laughs )
WELL, HOW THE MIGHTY
HAVE FALLEN.
THIS SNIVELING WHELP CAN'T
EVEN DRAW A PROPER BREATH NOW.
HE'LL BE CAUSING
NO MORE MISCHIEF WITH HIS HAMON.
THIS IS WHAT HE GETS
FOR CROSSING YOU, LORD DIO.
NOW WE ARE GOING TO PLAY.
OR MAYBE I'LL JUST
SIT QUIETLY AND WATCH
WHILE HE SUFFOCATES SLOWLY.
( chuckles )
Dio: SILENCE, WANG CHEN.
THERE SHALL BE
NO INSULT TO JOJO.
‐ Wang: HUH?
‐ Dio: HE IS THE ONE MAN
CAPABLE OF BRINGING ME
TO THE APEX OF MY FATE.
YOU WILL SHOW HIM ALL
THE RESPECT WHICH IS DUE TO HIM
BY SEVERING HIS HEAD
IN A PAINLESS MANNER.
Wang: OF COURSE, LORD DIO.
( chuckles )
Dio: THE BODY OF MY DEAREST FOE
HAS BECOME MY FUTURE!
‐ Erina: JONATHAN!
‐ ( JoJo gasping )
Dio: HE'S UP TO SOMETHING.
BE CAREFUL.
HE MIGHT HAVE ONE LAST TRICK
UP HIS MUSCLE‐BOUND SLEEVE.
Wang: BAH, HE'S DONE FOR.
LORD DIO OVERESTIMATES
HIS "MIGHTY POWER."
WELL, JONATHAN JOESTAR,
I'LL SCOOP OUT
WHAT LITTLE BRAINS YOU HAVE
WITH MY BARE FINGERS.
JoJo: MUST...
SAVE ERINA.
I HAVE TO USE THE LAST BIT
OF HAMON LEFT IN ME ALL AT ONCE.
PLEASE WORK.
Dio: CAREFUL.
WANG CHEN, LOOK OUT.
( Erina gasps )
‐ ( heart beats )
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
SOMETHING BROKE INSIDE MY BODY,
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
( Wang sputters )
Dio: WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
♪
JoJo: TH‐THIS IS THE END,
THE LAST HAMON I HAVE.
TOO WEAK TO DESTROY
THAT ZOMBIE COMPLETELY,
BUT IT WAS ENOUGH.
Dio: WHAT‐‐WHAT IS
HE PLAYING AT?
JOJO HAS INTERFERED
WITH WANG CHEN'S BODY,
DISRUPTING ITS FUNCTIONS
WITHOUT BRINGING IT
TO COMPLETE DESTRUCTION.
HE'S MADE IT SEIZE TIGHTLY
ONTO A PIECE OF MACHINERY,
AND THE DEVICE
IT CLINGS TO SO IMMOVABLY...
IS THE PADDLE'S SCREW SHAFT.
THE STRENGTH OF A ZOMBIE
IS SUFFICIENT
TO ARREST THE PADDLE.
IF THE SHAFT IS STOPPED,
STEAM PRESSURE IN THE PISTON
WILL BUILD UP INEXORABLY.
UNDER SUCH CONDITIONS,
THERE IS BUT ONE END.
THE SHIP WILL EXPLODE!
Erina: JONATHAN,
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING TO US?
JoJo: Y‐YOU MUST LEAVE, ERINA.
SOON THE SHIP
WILL BE DESTROYED.
Erina: I DON'T KNOW
HOW THE THINGS
THAT ARE OCCURRING TODAY
ARE POSSIBLE.
IT'S ALL TOO IMPOSSIBLE TO BEAR.
I DON'T KNOW
WHETHER I SHOULD CRY OR SCREAM.
PERHAPS I SHOULD JUST FAINT
DEAD AWAY AND BLOCK IT OUT.
BUT THERE IS ONE THING I KNOW.
ERINA JOESTAR...
WILL REMAIN WITH HER HUSBAND.
♪
IN THE WARMTH OF THESE LIPS,
I FEEL THE COOL EBBING
OF HIS LIFE.
JONATHAN JOESTAR IS DYING,
BUT WE ARE TOGETHER.
I WANT TO STAY LIKE THIS
UNTIL THE SHIP EXPLODES
AND EVERYTHING BURNS TO ASH,
UNTIL EVERYTHING IS GONE.
( machinery creaking )
( baby crying )
( Erina gasps )
JoJo: IT'S ALL RIGHT IF YOU CRY,
BUT YOU HAVE TO...
STAY ALIVE AND GO ON.
( Erina gasps )
JUST LIKE IN A STORYBOOK.
YOU WANT ME TO COME TO THE AID
OF A HELPLESS CHILD
AND ESCAPE TO SAFETY?
( sobs )
THAT'S UNFAIR,
JUST SHEER CRUELTY.
THE ONLY THING THAT I WANT
IS TO END MY LIFE HERE WITH YOU.
JoJo: THAT WOMAN DIED
TRYING TO SAVE HER CHILD
UNTIL THE LAST.
MY OWN MOTHER
DID THE SAME THING FOR ME.
SAVE YOURSELF
TAKE THE BABY. HURRY.
Dio: SO YOUR PLAN IS
TO DESTROY THIS VESSEL, IS IT?
JOJO, YOU NEVER GIVE UP
OR GIVE IN,
NO MATTER THE ODDS,
BUT KNOW THIS.
DETERMINATION
IS NOT JUST IN YOU.
I WILL LIVE.
THERE IS NO ONE WHO CAN DEFY ME!
I WILL TAKE YOUR BODY
AS MY OWN!
ZOMBIES, HITHER!
( zombies growling )
Dio: DEVOUR WANG CHEN'S BODY,
AND RESTART THE PISTON
ONCE YOU HAVE.
JoJo: THE END HAS BEGUN.
‐ ( Dio gasps )
‐ ( steam hissing )
‐ ( Erina gasps )
‐ ( JoJo grunts )
( gags )
( Erina gasps ) JONATHAN.
( JoJo sighs )
( Dio groans )
IT'S ALREADY BLOWING APART.
BUT THERE'S STILL A WAY OUT.
I WAS PROTECTING MYSELF FROM
THE SUN'S RAYS WELL BEFORE THIS.
LET IT EXPLODE.
I ALREADY HAVE
EVERYTHING I NEED TO SURVIVE.
( JoJo gags )
‐ ( baby crying )
‐ ( Erina gasps )
Dio: ERINA, TAKE A GOOD LOOK.
HAH! SINCE JOJO CAN
NO LONGER USE HIS HAMON,
I'LL REMOVE HIS HEAD
AND TAKE HIS BODY AS MY OWN.
THEN I SHALL WALK OVER AND
LIE DOWN IN MY VELVET BOUDOIR.
THAT HUMBLE SHELTER IS
MARVELOUSLY CONSTRUCTED.
IT COULD WITHSTAND
A TON OF DYNAMITE.
GOODBYE, JOJO,
AND WELCOME TO YOU,
MY NEW ETERNAL BODY!
( gags )
Erina: JONATHAN!
( gasps )
JoJo: DIO.
( Dio sputters )
JoJo: AS YOU OBSERVED,
IT MAY BE TRUE THAT OUR FATE
IS TO BE TOGETHER.
I FEEL AN ODD WARMTH FOR YOU,
FOR NOW OUR LIVES ARE
INTERWOVEN COMPLETELY
AND WILL END
ALONG WITH THIS SHIP.
( Erina sobbing )
FAREWELL TO YOU, MY BELOVED.
( Erina gasps, yelps )
Dio: JOJO, LET ME GO!
RELEASE ME.
THINK OF WHAT
WE TWO CAN ACHIEVE.
YOU'D LIKE A TASTE OF ETERNITY,
WOULD YOU NOT?
I CAN HEAL YOUR WOUNDS.
YOU AND ERINA
CAN LIVE TOGETHER FOREVER!
JOJO!
♪
NO. IT'S TOO LATE.
HE'S DEAD.
♪
Erina: JONATHAN JOESTAR
PASSED AWAY
INTO UNDESERVED OBLIVION.
HIS LIFE WAS
AN IMPORTANT PART OF HISTORY,
BUT INVISIBLE
TO ORDINARY PEOPLE.
MOST OF HUMANITY,
FOR WHOM HE SACRIFICED,
WILL NEVER KNOW
OF HIS NOBLE ACCOMPLISHMENTS...
BUT HIS DESCENDANTS WILL.
♪
( baby coos )
Erina: THE LIFE WITHIN ME,
NEWLY CREATED BY JONATHAN AND I,
WILL CERTAINLY HEAR HIS STORY.
Narrator: ERINA JOESTAR
WAS SOON RESCUED
AFLOAT NEAR THE CANARY ISLANDS,
AND THE BOOK OF THE STONE MASK
WAS CLOSED FOR A TIME.
BUT THAT WAS ONLY THE BEGINNING
OF A NEW BIZARRE ADVENTURE.
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Man: IT WAS IN THE FALL OF 1938.
Man #2: IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, SPEEDWAGON.
Man #3: YOU BASTARD!
HOW COULD YOU
HAVE POSSIBLY
HAVE KNOWN WHERE THEY WERE?
‐ Woman: TEACH HIM A LESSON.
‐ JoJo: JOSEPH JOESTAR.
MY FRIENDS CALL ME JOJO.