( JoJo groaning )
PHEW, I THINK I USED MY HEAD
A LITTLE BIT TOO MUCH LAST TIME.
MY SHOULDERS ARE REAL SORE.
THEY FEEL SO HEAVY.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Lisa Lisa: THE SUN IS UP.
THE TESTS ARE ENDING,
AND SOON THE TWO STUDENTS,
CAESAR AND JOJO, WILL BE
MAKING THEIR WAY BACK HERE.
Suzie Q: SIGNORA LISA LISA.
WHICH BLOUSE DO YOU LIKE TODAY?
Lisa Lisa: OH, I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
Suzie Q: WELL,
WHITE IS ALWAYS NICE,
BUT I THINK SOMETHING COLORFUL
CAN BE KIND OF FUN, TOO.
Lisa Lisa: I'LL LET YOU DECIDE.
Suzie Q: OKAY, LET'S SEE.
I THINK THE WHITE ONE
IS PRETTY,
BUT I REALLY LIKE
THE LOVELY DESIGN ON THIS ONE.
Lisa Lisa: I WONDER
IF JOJO AND CAESAR
HAVE PASSED THEIR FINAL EXAMS.
I HAVE A BAD FEELING.
I'M BEGINNING TO WORRY.
Suzie Q: SO TODAY WE'RE GOING
TO GO WITH THE PRETTY WHITE.
‐ Lisa Lisa: SUZIE Q...
‐ Suzie Q: YES?
Lisa Lisa: PLEASE SEND
CAESAR AND JOJO TO MY ROOM
AS SOON AS THEY ARRIVE.
Suzie Q:
YES, OF COURSE, SIGNORA.
HMM. I KNOW I SAID
I LIKE THE WHITE BLOUSE,
BUT THE OTHER ONE IS NICE, TOO.
SO WHICH IS BETTER?
OH, WHICH DO I CHOOSE?
WHITE. BUT THEN AGAIN,
THIS IS REALLY NICE, TOO.
AI! WHAT DO I DO?
Lisa Lisa: THE COLORFUL ONE
WILL DO NICELY. THANK YOU.
Suzie Q: EXCELLENT CHOICE.
♪
I'LL JUST LEAVE THESE HERE
FOR YOU, ALL RIGHT?
I'LL COME BACK LATER
AND CLEAN UP THE BROKEN GLASS.
BE CAREFUL, OKAY?
Lisa Lisa: I WILL. THANK YOU.
( door opens )
♪
JoJo: HEY.
SUZIE Q.
( Suzie Q screams )
JoJo: EH, WHAT ARE
YOU SCREAMING FOR?
BE QUIET, YOU STUPID IDIOT.
Suzie Q: W‐WHO‐‐WHO ARE YOU?
TH‐THERE'S A STRANGER
ON THE ISLAND!
JoJo: HEY, WAIT.
YOU THINK I'M A STRANGER?
‐ Suzie Q: HUH?
‐ JoJo: IT'S ME, YOU DUMMY,
‐ JOSEPH JOESTAR.
‐ Suzie Q: HUH?
JoJo: HMM.
Suzie Q: JOJO? NO WAY.
WHEN I SAW YOU BEFORE,
YOU WERE ALWAYS WEARING A MASK.
WOW, WHAT A SURPRISE.
JoJo: WHAT? ARE YOU TELLING ME
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN MY FACE
IN ALL THIS TIME?
( laughs )
SO? WHAT DO YOU THINK?
AM I HANDSOME?
Suzie Q: HMM.
WEIRD LIPS.
‐ JoJo: GUH!
‐ ( Suzie Q giggles )
JoJo: WELL, THEY MAY BE WEIRD,
BUT IF WE WERE EVER TO FALL
MADLY IN LOVE WITH EACH OTHER,
YOU'D BE WELCOME
TO KISS THEM ALL YOU'D LIKE.
( Suzie Q giggles )
YEAH, IN YOUR DREAMS.
( giggles ) AHH!
( JoJo laughs )
‐ ( Suzie Q gasps )
‐ JoJo: HMM?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
( stammers )
UH, NOTHING AT ALL, REALLY.
OH! YEAH, SIGNORA LISA LISA
WANTS YOU TO GO
UP TO HER ROOM RIGHT AWAY.
BUT SHE IS TAKING A BATH,
SO YOU SHOULD PROBABLY WAIT
HALF AN HOUR.
JoJo: GOT IT.
I WAS PLANNING TO GO ANYWAY.
I'VE GOTTA TELL HER THAT THEY
KNOW ALL ABOUT THE STONE.
Suzie Q: HUH?
OH, NO,
YOU'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT HER STONE, ARE YOU?
JoJo: UH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU REALLY DON'T WANT TO GET
INVOLVED IN ALL THIS STUFF.
‐ BELIEVE ME.
‐ Suzie Q: UH, OKAY.
JOJO, WAIT A MINUTE.
JoJo: HUH? WHAT'S UP?
( Suzie Q sighs )
YOU'RE ACTUALLY
PRETTY HOT, YOU KNOW?
JoJo: HMM?
HMM. ( grunts )
HMM. THAT'S ODD.
MY SHOULDERS FEEL LIKE THEY'VE
SUDDENLY STARTED TO LOOSEN UP.
♪
THE NEWS I HAVE TO REPORT
IS REALLY IMPORTANT,
BUT LISA LISA IS TAKING A BATH,
SO I'M GONNA HAVE TO WAIT
FOR HALF AN HOUR
UNTIL SHE'S DONE.
♪
( chuckles )
IF I WAS TOLD TO WAIT,
THEN WAITING IS WHAT I'LL DO.
NOW WHERE TO SPEND HALF AN HOUR?
I THINK THE BEST PLACE
IS HERE BY LISA LISA'S DOOR.
WOULD IT REALLY
BE ALL THAT WRONG
IF I TOOK A PEEK THROUGH
THE KEYHOLE TO CHECK THINGS OUT?
( gasping, chuckling )
NICE.
( laughs )
UH, EH?
SUZIE Q?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT'S SHE DOING IN THERE?
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE HER
GO INTO THE ROOM.
THAT WAS REALLY FAST.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS
STILL OUT ON THE DOCKS.
HUH?
WHAT THE HELL?
THE DOORKNOB IS COMPLETELY
COVERED IN SOME KIND OF GOO.
♪
Lisa Lisa: SUZIE Q, TELL ME,
HAVE JOJO AND CAESAR
MADE IT BACK YET?
UH, SUZIE Q?
( gasps )
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, SUZIE Q?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT DID YOU DO
WITH THE RED STONE? ( gasps )
( bones popping )
( gagging )
Lisa Lisa: WHO ARE YOU?!
TELL ME WHAT YOU
DID WITH THE RED STONE!
‐ JoJo: NO. THIS IS BAD.
‐ ( gagging )
Lisa Lisa: IT SEEMS SOMETHING
HAS TAKEN OVER SUZIE Q'S BODY.
( gasps )
Esidisi and Suzie Q: YOU,
YOU HAVE REDUCED ME TO NOTHING
BUT A BRAIN WITH NO BODY
OF MY OWN!
BUT NEVERTHELESS I
CHALLENGE YOU TO ONE LAST FIGHT!
I PUT THE STONE ON THE BOAT
THAT JUST LEFT THE DOCK.
I AM HERE TO STOP YOU FROM
CHASING IT AND GETTING IT BACK.
I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU
TO FOLLOW THAT POSTAL BOAT,
NO MATTER WHAT!
THE WOMAN I AM INSIDE OF
IS STILL MOSTLY ALIVE, YOU SEE.
‐ ( Lisa Lisa gasps )
‐ Esidisi: THERE IS ONLY ONE WAY
FOR YOU
TO DESTROY ME COMPLETELY,
AND THAT IS
TO TAKE HER LIFE AS WELL.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
ARE YOU CAPABLE OF THAT?!
( laughs )
JoJo: ESIDISI!
Lisa Lisa: JOJO.
JoJo: YOU WON'T STOP
COMING AT US, WILL YOU?
YOU DON'T GIVE UP.
‐ Caesar: JOJO.
‐ JoJo: EH?
OH, CAESAR.
WELL, IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME.
( Caesar gasps )
YOU, UH‐‐
( coughs, clears throat )
SO YOU MANAGED TO SURVIVE
YOUR BOUT WITH ESIDISI?
YOU'RE A LUCKY ONE,
THAT'S FOR‐‐
( gasps )
JOJO. WHAT THE HELL
WERE YOU DOING IN HERE
WITH OUR COACH?
JoJo: HEY, COOL IT,
YOU MEATHEAD.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT, OKAY?
JUST TAKE A LOOK AT SUZIE Q.
Caesar: ALL RIGHT THEN.
( Suzie Q crying )
Caesar: WHAT'S GOING ON?
JoJo: IT'S ESIDISI.
DAMN HIM.
HE SOMEHOW FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO MAKE HIS BRAIN
AND BLOOD VESSELS
INVADE HER BODY
AND TAKE CONTROL OF HER.
Suzie Q: SAVE ME, CAESAR!
( Caesar gasps )
Suzie Q: OH, PLEASE HELP ME.
EVERYONE PICKS ON ME
ALL THE TIME.
BUT YOU'LL NEVER PICK ON ME,
CAESAR, WILL YOU?
JoJo: DON'T FALL
FOR A WORD OF IT.
SUZIE Q'S NOT DOING THE TALKING.
ESIDISI IS MANIPULATING HER.
Lisa Lisa: THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE MANAGED TO TAKE THE STONE
AND PUT IT ON A POSTAL BOAT.
LEAVE THIS THING TO JOJO AND ME,
AND FIND THAT BOAT.
GET THE STONE BACK.
IF THE RED STONE REACHES VENICE
AND IS TRANSFERRED
ONTO A TRAIN,
WE'LL LOSE TRACK OF IT
AND HAVE NO WAY TO KNOW
WHERE IT WILL END UP.
( Esidisi grunts )
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE,
DICKHEADS!
IF YOU WANT TO STOP
THAT BOAT OR LEAVE AT ALL,
YOU'LL HAVE TO KILL ME FIRST!
( Caesar gasps )
A MALE VOICE.
I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
HIS BLOOD VESSELS MUST BE
CONTROLLING HER FROM THE INSIDE.
( Esidisi laughs )
YEAH, COME ON! BRING IT!
USE YOUR HAMON, AND KILL ME!
IT SHOULD BE
A RELATIVELY EASY TASK
FOR YOU TO DESTROY ME
IN MY CURRENT STATE.
BUT THEN AGAIN, YOU MUST KNOW
THAT THIS GIRL'S HEART
ISN'T NEARLY STRONG ENOUGH
TO ENDURE A HAMON SHOCK
AND SURVIVE IT.
ARE YOU WILLING
TO SNUFF OUT THIS GIRL'S LIFE
IN ORDER TO DEFEAT ME?
IF YOU ARE,
THEN HURRY UP, AND DO IT!
QUIT STANDING THERE
AND WASTING TIME,
YOU STUPID DICKHEADS!
( laughs )
JoJo: HEY.
I'M NOT SOFTHEARTED, ESIDISI.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS END
THE LIFE OF ONE YOUNG GIRL,
AND I'LL BE ABLE TO SAVE
THE ENTIRE WORLD FROM YOU.
I WOULD CONSIDER IT A SMALL,
BUT NECESSARY SACRIFICE.
Caesar: WAIT A MINUTE!
ARE YOU SERIOUS, JOJO?
JoJo: TIME TO TEAR YOU INTO
LITTLE, TINY PIECES, ESIDISI!
‐ Lisa Lisa: NO, YOU CAN'T!
‐ Caesar: JOJO!
JoJo: I'M NOT KIDDING HERE!
I'M REALLY GONNA DO IT!
( gasps ) DAMN IT ALL.
I JUST CAN'T HIT HER.
THE BASTARD.
I THOUGHT HE'D POP OUT OF HER
WHEN I STARTED TO MAKE MY MOVE,
BUT IT DIDN'T EVEN FAZE HIM.
♪
Esidisi:
ENOUGH OF YOUR BLUFFING.
YOU COULD NEVER KILL THIS GIRL,
NO MATTER HOW HARD YOU TRIED.
( chuckling )
Esidisi: BY NOW,
I'M SURE THE STONE
HAS ALREADY ARRIVED
ON THE MAIN ISLAND.
YOU'RE TOO LATE.
HEH. AND NOW...
( both gasp )
Caesar: THE BASTARD.
WHAT IS HE DOING TO SUZIE Q NOW?
JoJo: STOP!
DON'T DO THIS, ESIDISI!
Esidisi: AND NOW,
JUST TO MAKE THINGS INTERESTING,
I WILL MAKE THIS GIRL'S BODY
EXPLODE AND COVER YOU ALL
IN BLOOD THAT BURNS
AS HOT AS FLOWING LAVA!
JoJo: LOOK OUT!
HIS BLOOD IS BOILING HOT.
Lisa Lisa: SUZIE Q'S BODY,
IT'S BEGINNING TO FALL APART!
IF THIS KEEPS UP,
IT WON'T BE JUST SUZIE Q
WHO'LL BE IN TROUBLE.
IT'LL BE ALL OF US AS WELL.
SO WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
JOJO, YOU NEED TO USE
YOUR HAMON ON HER RIGHT NOW.
( JoJo gasps )
COME ON. NO.
I DON'T WANNA DO THIS.
PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME.
I'M STILL HAVING TO DEAL
WITH ALL
THE HORRIBLE NIGHTMARES I GET
ABOUT THE TIME I CHOPPED
VON STROHEIM'S LEG OFF.
A DIFFERENT PLAN.
WE NEED A DIFFERENT PLAN
RIGHT NOW.
( Esidisi groaning )
Lisa Lisa: ALL RIGHT.
I'LL DO IT, THEN.
Caesar: NO, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
COACH, LET ME DO IT.
JoJo: WAIT. DON'T DO ANYTHING.
I THOUGHT OF SOMETHING.
CAESAR, DO YOU REMEMBER
HELL CLIMB PILLAR?
WE CAN GIVE THAT A SHOT.
IT'S DO OR DIE,
SO LET'S GO FOR IT.
‐ Caesar: EH?
‐ JoJo: YOU AND ME,
TWO TYPES OF HAMON
AT THE SAME TIME.
Lisa Lisa: TWO TYPES? ( gasps )
Caesar: YEAH, I SEE
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
YOU'RE RIGHT. SOMETHING
LIKE THAT MIGHT JUST WORK.
JoJo: YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO THEN.
( Esidisi wails )
‐ ( both gasp )
‐ Lisa Lisa: JOJO! CAESAR!
Caesar: RIGHT, I UNDERSTAND.
JOJO, I WANT YOU
TO FOLLOW MY BREATHING.
( JoJo grunts )
Caesar: LET'S GO!
( JoJo yells )
( Caesar yells )
♪
Narrator: JOJO CREATES
A BURST OF POSITIVE HAMON
AND SURROUNDS SUZIE Q WITH IT.
CAESAR CREATES
A BURST OF NEGATIVE HAMON
FOCUSED ON HER HEART.
AT THAT POINT, THE HAMON IS BOTH
NEGATIVE AND POSITIVE ZERO.
( Suzie Q gasps )
♪
Lisa Lisa: IT WORKED.
YOU FORCED ESIDISI OUT.
Caesar: JOJO!
JoJo: DON'T WORRY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL JUST LET THE SUN
TAKE CARE OF THE REST.
Caesar:
THAT LOWDOWN, DIRTY SCUM,
HIDING IN A GIRL'S BODY
LIKE THAT.
HE'S NOTHING BUT A COWARD.
JoJo: NO, CAESAR.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
I FOUGHT AGAINST HIM,
SO I UNDERSTAND.
YOU SEE, HE GAVE ALL HE HAD
AND EVEN THREW AWAY HIS PRIDE,
BECAUSE HE FELT A DUTY
TO GET THE STONE FOR HIS ALLIES.
FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS,
HE DID AS HE PLEASED,
AND HE LIVED HIS LIFE
TO ITS FULLEST.
WHETHER IT WAS GOOD OR EVIL,
I RESPECT HIS LIFE
AND HOW HE CHOSE TO LIVE IT.
♪
( sighs )
Caesar: JOJO.
( Hamon crackles )
Lisa Lisa: SUZIE Q...
WHILE ESIDISI CONTROLLED YOU,
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN AT LEAST
SEMICONSCIOUS MOST OF THE TIME.
NOW TELL ME,
WHERE IS THE STONE HEADED?
( Suzie Q groans )
SWITZERLAND...
ST. MORITZ.
A PACKAGE...
AN ENVELOPE
WITH SIGNORA LISA LISA'S CREST.
THE ADDRESS IS...
JoJo: SWITZERLAND?
Caesar: WHAT ABOUT
KARS AND WAMUU? ARE THEY THERE?
Meshina: MM. I JUST CHECKED
WITH MY CONTACT AT THE STATION.
A CARGO TRAIN FOR SWITZERLAND
LEFT NOT 10 MINUTES AGO.
JoJo: THAT'S IT. THE STONE HAS
TO BE SOMEWHERE ON THAT TRAIN.
THEY'VE GOT A BIG HEAD START,
BUT WE'VE GOT
TO SOMEHOW FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO GET OURSELVES TO ST. MORITZ
BEFORE THAT TRAIN ARRIVES.
Lisa Lisa: WE HAVE TO DO
EVERYTHING WE CAN
TO KEEP THE STONE FROM FALLING
INTO THE WRONG HANDS.
WE MIGHT EVEN HAVE TO DO
A LITTLE BIT OF DIRTY WORK.
A FEW LAWS
MIGHT BE BROKEN AS WELL.
SOME OF US MAY EVEN
END UP IN BODY BAGS.
JoJo: DON'T WORRY. I WON'T.
Caesar: I WASN'T READY BEFORE,
BUT NOW THERE'S
NO WAY I'M GONNA LOSE.
Meshina: I'LL ERADICATE
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
Lisa Lisa: LET'S GO!
Caesar: RIGHT.
WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
( engine roars )
♪
( tires squeal )
JoJo: HEY, SUZIE Q,
LOOK OVER HERE!
‐ ( car horn honks )
‐ ( Suzie Q gasps )
JoJo: IT'S GOODBYE
FOR NOW, SUZIE Q.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN OR HOW,
BUT I'LL BE BACK IN VENICE
ONE DAY, I PROMISE.
Suzie Q: REALLY?
JoJo: YEAH.
HEAL THOSE UGLY WOUNDS
ON YOUR FACE
BEFORE I GET BACK, WILL YOU?
( Suzie Q sighs )
( crying )
JoJo: LATER!
Suzie Q: JOJO, BE CAREFUL!
MAKE SURE YOU COME BACK
IN ONE PIECE, OKAY?!
JoJo: DON'T GET PUSHY.
YOU MAY BE AN OLD LADY BEFORE
I GET BACK, BUT I WILL RETURN.
Suzie Q: OH, YEAH?
YOU STUPID JERK!
JoJo: I'LL BE BACK
A LOT SOONER THAN YOU THINK.
♪
( dog whimpering )
( rumble )
‐ ( driver laughs )
‐ ( passenger chuckles )
( tires squeal )
Passenger: HEY,
DRIVE THE DAMNED CAR, WILL YOU?
Driver: HUH?
Passenger: WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR ARMS, MAN?
Driver: HUH? AAH!
SOMETHING'S WRONG
WITH THE WHEEL, MAN!
I CAN'T GET IT TO MOVE!
( both scream )
( crash )
Kars: HMM.
ESIDISI HASN'T REPORTED BACK.
HE LAST SAID
THAT HE HAD LEARNED
THE STONE WAS
SOMEWHERE IN VENICE.
I WONDER IF SOMETHING
HAS HAPPENED TO HIM.
Meshina: HEY, JOJO.
JOJO.
( JoJo snores, mutters )
Meshina: JOJO, WAKE UP.
JoJo: HUH? WHA...
Caesar: JOJO,
WE'VE CAUGHT UP WITH THE TRAIN.
Meshina: THEY'RE GOING THROUGH
THEIR CUSTOMS CHECK
AT THE MOMENT.
Lisa Lisa:
THAT WORKS IN OUR FAVOR.
WE'RE LESS THAN AN HOUR
FROM ST. MORITZ,
WHICH LEAVES US
ENOUGH TIME TO GET READY.
IT'S GOOD WE CAUGHT UP.
Caesar: COME ON, JOJO.
LOOK SHARP.
( car horn honking )
JoJo: LISTEN, I'M JUST
SAVING UP MY STRENGTH
FOR THE BIG BATTLE, THAT'S ALL.
GET OFF MY CASE.
LET'S HURRY UP AND GET THERE
SO WE CAN RETRIEVE THAT STONE.
THEN WE'RE GONNA NEED
SOME SORT OF PLAN
FOR THE FIGHT WITH WAMUU.
Caesar: WE'LL WAIT FOR THAT
UNTIL WE CROSS. ( gasps )
( honking continues )
JoJo: WHAT THE HELL?
‐ ( car door opens )
‐ KNOCK IT OFF!
IF YOU WANT TO GO ON,
JUST QUIT HONKING, AND PASS US.
( gasps ) GERMAN SOLDIERS.
WHAT THE HELL ARE THEY DOING
IN A CAR
ON THE SWISS‐ITALIAN BORDER?
( German laughs )
WELL, WELL,
YOU'RE LOOKING RATHER SPRY.
MY, YOU HAVE GROWN SO MUCH,
JOESTAR.
JoJo: HUH?
W‐WHAT DID YOU SAY, MISTER?
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
G‐GET BACK HERE!
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T KNOW
ANY GERMAN SOLDIERS.
Meshina: HEY, LOOK AT THE TRAIN.
JoJo: SO MANY SOLDIERS.
Soldier: HEY, MAJOR,
WE FOUND THE PACKAGE!
Lisa Lisa: THE CREST.
LOOK. THEY'VE GOT THE PACKAGE.
JoJo: YEAH, AND WE ALL
KNOW WHAT'S INSIDE.
♪
( Caesar gasps )
THE RED STONE OF AJA!
Lisa Lisa: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DO THE GERMANS WANT IT?
Major: WE HAVE DECIDED
TO TAKE THE STONE
AS A SPECIMEN FOR OUR
SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH PROGRAM.
FOR THE PAST THREE WEEKS,
WE HAVE BEEN WATCHING
YOUR EVERY MOVE
WHILE YOU WERE OPERATING
IN VENICE.
WE BEGAN THE SURVEILLANCE
WHEN WE LOST OUR TEAM IN ROME.
WE SAW YOUR TRAINING,
WE SAW ESIDISI,
AND WE KNEW
YOU WERE CHASING THE STONE.
NOW, OUR BASE IS SET UP
AT A LODGE UP AHEAD.
FOLLOW US.
WE WANT TO ASK A FEW QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE STONE UND ABOUT KARS.
WHY NOT WORK TOGETHER, EH?
AFTER ALL, WE ARE
NOT COMPLETE STRANGERS, JOJO.
JoJo: HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU BLABBERING ABOUT?
DON'T THINK YOU KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME, YOU BASTARD!
Meshina: IF THE GERMANS
ARE HERE, THAT MEANS...
Caesar: WHAT DO WE DO, COACH?
Lisa Lisa:
WE HAVE TO FOLLOW THEM.
AT LEAST WE KNOW KARS DOESN'T
HAVE THE RED STONE EITHER.
Narrator: AT THAT TIME,
THE GERMAN ARMY
WAS MARCHING ACROSS EUROPE,
TAKING COUNTRY AFTER COUNTRY.
THEY WANTED TO ENSURE
THEIR RULE ACROSS THE CONTINENT
WOULD LAST INDEFINITELY.
THE POWER OF THE MASK
AND RED STONE
WOULD SOLVE
THEIR PROBLEM PERFECTLY
BY GIVING THEM EVERYTHING
THEY WOULD NEED TO PREVAIL.
THE GERMANS WERE PLANNING TO USE
THE ULTIMATE POWER
OF IMMORTALITY
TO CONQUER THE WORLD.
♪
( footsteps crunching )
Kars: I'LL READ THE HEAT INSIDE.
THE FIREPLACE IS LIT.
FOUR LIGHTS ON THE WALL,
TWO ON THE CEILING,
TWO ON THE DESK. NO, THREE.
FOUR HUMANS STANDING
BY THE WALL.
THEIR HEIGHTS ARE 178, 174,
181, AND 178 CENTIMETERS.
ONE HUMAN IS BY THE FIREPLACE,
183 CENTIMETERS TALL.
THERE ARE FIVE HUMANS,
ALL MALE.
♪
ONE, TWO...
THAT'S FOUR
AND FIVE.
Major: SO YOU MUST BE KARS.
YOU'RE FAST.
IN JUST A FEW HOURS, YOU HEARD
ABOUT YOUR FRIEND'S DEFEAT,
LEARNED THAT WE
HAD OBTAINED THE STONE,
FOUND OUR LOCATION,
AND HAVE COME FOR IT.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
AND THEN THIS BRUTAL,
PERFECTLY CALCULATED ASSAULT.
NOT ONE OF MY MEN
MADE EVEN THE SLIGHTEST SOUND
BEFORE THEY DIED.
Kars: I WAS SURE THERE WERE
ONLY FIVE MEN IN THIS ROOM.
NOW TELL ME, WHY CAN'T I
SENSE YOUR BODY HEAT? ( grunts )
JoJo: HEY, RIFLE HEADS,
WHAT'S A GUY GOTTA DO
TO GET A LITTLE FOOD IN HERE?
KARS!
Kars: HUH?
THIS MAN'S MECHANICAL.
JoJo: WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE VON STROHEIM!
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Caesar: WE SHOULD ATTACK NOW.
Lisa Lisa: THE BUILDING ON TOP
OF THAT HILL IS THE ADDRESS.
JoJo: THAT WAS PRETTY MEAN.
Von Stroheim: GERMAN SCIENCE
IS THE FINEST IN THE WORLD!
Kars: NO MACHINE CAN STOP ME.