Speedwagon: JOJO WON HIS BATTLE
AGAINST THAT DEMON.
POOR SOD.
HE LOST EVERYTHING
IN THE PROCESS.
THAT'S WHY I BROUGHT HIM HERE
THREE DAYS AGO.
AND NOW, BEREFT OF FATHER
AND HOME ALIKE,
HOW'S HE GONNA MUSTER UP
THE WILL TO LIVE?
DON'T GIVE UP
ON THE WORLD YET, JOJO!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( cane tapping )
SPIRIT...
THAT'S WHAT HE NEEDS,
SO I'M GONNA GIVE IT TO HIM.
HUH?
IT'S THE DEAD OF NIGHT,
BUT THERE'S A LAMP BURNING
IN HIS ROOM.
♪
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
HOW LONG'S SHE BEEN AT IT?
DON'T TELL ME SHE'S BEEN
WATCHING OVER HIM ALL THIS TIME.
( gasps ) HER FINGERS,
CRACKED FROM THE DAMP,
I'D WAGER.
SHE MUST HAVE BEEN COOLING
HIS BURNS ROUND THE CLOCK
FOR THEM TO GET LIKE THAT LIKE.
‐ ( JoJo sighs )
‐ ( Erina gasps )
THANK GOODNESS.
( Speedwagon gasps )
HE'S AWAKE.
Erina: YOU'RE THROUGH
THE WORST OF IT.
YOU SHOULD BE FINE.
JoJo: SO YOU'VE BEEN
TENDING TO MY INJURIES?
BUT HOW CAN‐‐HOW CAN
YOU BE STANDING HERE?
YOU'RE THE IMAGE OF‐‐
BUT NO. I'M SORRY.
YOUR FACE REMINDS ME
OF A GIRL I USED TO KNOW.
HER NAME WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO BE
ERINA PENDLETON, WOULD IT?
JoJo: IT'S YOU.
Erina: IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME,
JONATHAN JOESTAR...
JOJO.
JoJo: ERINA,
YOU'VE REALLY GROWN UP.
Erina: ME? BUT YOU'VE GROWN
A FAIR SIGHT MORE.
YET...
YOU'RE STILL THE BOY YOU WERE.
JoJo: YEAH.
Speedwagon: SHE MAKES
A BETTER FLORENCE NIGHTINGALE
THAN I DO ANYHOW.
YOU REST UP, JOJO.
TIME FOR SPEEDWAGON
TO MAKE HIS EXIT.
( Erina gasps )
I‐‐I MUST HAVE FAINTED
FOR A MOMENT.
( gasps ) BUT YOUR ARM,
IT'S BROKEN.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE CAUGHT ME.
( JoJo chuckles )
YOU CAUGHT ME LONG AGO.
Speedwagon:
I DARESAY OL' JOJO
WON'T BE LACKING A REASON
TO LIVE AFTER THIS REUNION.
♪
Man: YOU SHOULD HAVE MADE
AN EARLY NIGHT OF IT,
YOU HARLOT. BIG MISTAKE.
( woman screams )
( Jack laughs )
Dio: MOST MEN SHACKLE THEMSELVES
TO PETTY MORALITY.
Jack: HUH?
Dio: THEY FEAR
THE CONSEQUENCES OF THEIR EVIL.
‐ ( apothecary laughs )
‐ Dio: BUT SOME ARE UNFETTERED
BY MAN'S LAWS
IN ALL THEIR TYRANNY.
THEY ARE THE VANGUARD.
BECOME MY SERVANT,
JACK THE RIPPER.
YOU'VE NO FURTHER NEED
FOR FREE WILL.
( Jack groans )
Dio: I WILL MAKE YOU
AN INSTRUMENT OF DEATH
THE LIKES OF WHICH
YOU CAN'T BEGIN TO IMAGINE.
Jack: DO IT.
Dio: AS FOR WHAT
I SHALL TAKE IN RETURN...
( squelching )
JoJo: ONLY SPEEDWAGON AND I
KNOW WHAT TRULY
TOOK PLACE HERE THAT NIGHT.
DIO WAS CONSUMED IN THE INFERNO,
BUT WHAT OF THE ACCURSED MASK?
NO SIGN OF IT IN THE RUBBLE.
SMASHED BY FALLING MASONRY?
I HOPE SO. I WANT TO PUT
THIS NIGHTMARE BEHIND ME.
Erina: JOJO.
JoJo: ERINA.
HMM?
THAT MAN, HE HAUNTS OUR STEPS.
Erina: IS SOMETHING WRONG?
JoJo: NO. ALL IS WELL.
( gasps )
♪
Man: AH, SIGNORE JOESTAR.
AND THE LASS AT YOUR SIDE
IS SIGNORINA PENDLETON.
( man grunts )
( JoJo gasps )
WHO ARE YOU?!
Man: YOU SURVIVED
AGAINST THE MASK.
NOT MANY MEN CAN CLAIM THAT.
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( man yells )
‐ ( JoJo yelps )
‐ Erina: JOJO!
( JoJo gasping )
‐ ( coughs )
‐ Man: THAT'S RIGHT.
LET THE SHOCK OF THAT IMPACT
PUSH ALL THE AIR FROM YOUR BODY.
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ Erina: JOJO! WHY?
HE WAS ALREADY HURT, YOU CAD!
Man: IT'S TRUE
I KNOCKED THE AIR OUT OF HIM,
BUT HE'LL THANK ME FOR IT.
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( bones cracking )
MY ARM!
WHAT IS THIS? MY BROKEN BONES...
FEEL LIKE THEY'RE MENDING!
Zeppeli: BARON ZEPPELI,
AT YOUR SERVICE.
COURAGE ALONE WILL NOT BE
ENOUGH TO BEAT THE MASK.
JoJo: MY ARM WAS SHATTERED,
BUT NOW...
THE PAIN HAS SUBSIDED.
LIFTING THIS ROCK IS NOTHING.
Erina: THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
JoJo: SIR, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
AND WHAT IS HAPPENING TO ME?
Zeppeli: PLEASE,
TRY TO LIMIT YOURSELF
TO ONE QUESTION AT A TIME.
YOU HEALED YOURSELF, JOJO.
HOW YOU BREATHED
AFTER I POKED YOU WAS THE KEY.
( sneezes )
JoJo: BUT WHY DID YOU GO TO
THE TROUBLE IN THE FIRST PLACE?
AND HOW DO YOU KNOW
WHO I‐‐HE'S GONE.
Zeppeli: WHAT PART OF "ONE
QUESTION AT A TIME" ELUDED YOU?
YOU'LL GET THE ANSWERS
YOU DESIRE, AMICO. FOLLOW ME.
THIS DAY, I WILL SHOW YOU THINGS
THE LIKES OF WHICH WILL CHANGE
YOUR DESTINY FOREVER.
( JoJo gasps )
Zeppeli: IT WAS WITH GOOD REASON
THAT I STRUCK YOU
IN THE DIAPHRAGM.
THE SHOCK OF THE IMPACT
ALTERED YOUR BREATHING.
JoJo: BUT HOW DID THAT
HEAL MY ARM?
Zeppeli: WITH THE ENERGY I AM
ABOUT TO DEMONSTRATE FOR YOU.
♪
JoJo: WAIT.
WHAT MISCHIEF IS HE PLANNING?
( Zeppeli breathing deeply )
( grunting )
( yelling )
JoJo: LOOK AT HIM, ERINA.
HIS LEGS. THOSE RIPPLES.
I'VE NEVER SEEN WATER DO THAT.
Zeppeli: WHAT YOU SEE IS
THE FORCE THAT EASED YOUR PAIN
AND HEALED YOUR BROKEN BONES,
SIGNORE JOESTAR.
( yells )
‐ JoJo: DON'T DO IT!
‐ ( Erina screams )
( Zeppeli chuckles )
( yells )
( frog croaking )
( JoJo gasps )
THAT FROG SEEMS NONE THE WORSE.
Zeppeli: THAT WAS SENDO YOU SAW.
JoJo: WAIT. "SENDO"?
Zeppeli: IT'S RIPPLE ENERGY
CREATED BY HAMON.
I SENT MY HAMON COURSING
HARMLESSLY THROUGH FROGGY
TO SPLIT MY REAL TARGET,
THE ROCK BELOW.
JOJO, I KNOW FOR A FACT
THE STONE MASK
WAS NOT DESTROYED.
DIO BRANDO KEEPS IT
CLOSE TO HIM EVEN NOW.
JoJo: NO, IT CAN'T BE.
BARON, IS DIO STILL ALIVE?
Zeppeli: INDEED,
AND HE HOLDS THE MASK
I HAVE SOUGHT FOR DECADES NOW.
THAT MASK MUST BE DESTROYED,
AND ITS MASTER
MUST BE REDUCED TO ASH.
IT IS YOUR DESTINY TO FIGHT
FOR THIS RIGHTEOUS CAUSE.
YOU WILL LEARN TO WIELD SENDO,
OR YOU WILL DIE.
THE FUTURE OF HUMANITY
IS AT STAKE!
JoJo: MY DESTINY?
Erina: WHAT IS HE TALKING ABOUT?
NONE OF IT MAKES ANY SENSE.
( JoJo gasps )
( thinking )
ERINA.
SHE'S ALREADY SUFFERED
ENOUGH AT DIO'S HANDS.
I CAN'T DRAG HER INTO THIS.
( Zeppeli gasps )
INCREDIBLE.
IT'S BLOSSOMING!
HE'S PASSING THE SPARE
HAMON ENERGY FROM HIS HEALED ARM
INTO THE BRANCH
AND SENDING IT INTO BLOOM.
AND AMAZINGLY HE DOESN'T
EVEN REALIZE HE'S DOING IT.
THIS BOY, HE IS A NATURAL.
OF WHAT MIGHT HE BE CAPABLE,
WITH THE PROPER REFINEMENT
OF HIS ABILITIES?
REJOICE, MANKIND.
THIS DAY, I MAY HAVE FOUND
YOUR CHAMPION.
( woman screams )
( body falls )
♪
Dio: MMM.
WITH EVERY MEAL,
I FEEL MY STRENGTH RETURNING.
WHAT A SIMPLE THING,
THE FOOD CHAIN.
AS PIGS FEED ON GRASS,
SO DOES MAN FEED UPON THEM,
AND I, AT THE TOP OF IT ALL,
FEED UPON THE HUMANS.
THEY EXIST TO SERVE ME
AND QUELL MY THIRST.
GO, JACK. IT'S SUPPERTIME.
( Jack growls )
Dio: NOW TO SWELL THE RANKS
OF MY DIABOLICAL ARMY
AND SEND IT HENCE.
I WILL STAND ASTRIDE THIS WORLD.
HUMANITY WILL KNEEL
AT DIO BRANDO'S FEET.
♪
JoJo: AND SO I BEGAN
TO STUDY HAMON
UNDER THE TUTELAGE
OF THE MYSTERIOUS ZEPPELI.
THE TRAINING WAS SPARTAN,
BUT I HAD NO CHOICE.
HERE'S HOW IT CAME ABOUT.
Zeppeli: JOJO, MY HISTORY
WITH THE STONE MASK
HAS BEEN A LONG ONE.
I WAS YOUR AGE.
HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT WAS EVER THE CASE NOW.
I HARBORED A GREAT THIRST
FOR ADVENTURE,
AS THE YOUNG SO OFTEN DO.
IT WAS MY GOOD FORTUNE
TO TRAVEL THE WORLD
AS A MEMBER OF MY FATHER'S
ARCHAEOLOGICAL TEAM.
WOULD THAT WE
HAD NEVER LAIN EYES
ON THOSE AZTEC RUINS THAT DAY.
JoJo: YOU'RE SAYING...
Zeppeli: YES.
THE HANDS THAT PULLED
THAT EVIL ARTIFACT
INTO THE LIGHT OF DAY
BELONGED TO ME.
ONE ILL‐FATED NIGHT
DURING THE VOYAGE HOME,
A MAN OF OUR NUMBER
SUCCUMBED TO HIS CURIOSITY
AND DONNED THE MASK.
‐ ( thunder crashes )
‐ ( man screams )
Zeppeli: THE CHANGE IN HIM
WAS IMMEDIATE.
RAMPAGING THROUGH THE SHIP,
HE RIPPED
HIS COMPANIONS' HEADS OFF
IN A BACCHANALIA OF BLOOD.
58 CREWMEN BUTCHERED
IN A MATTER OF MINUTES.
I DOVE INTO THE SEA TO ESCAPE,
BUT THE FIEND GAVE CHASE.
( creature roars )
( Zeppeli gasps )
SUDDENLY DAWN BROKE.
AS HE CRUMBLED TO DUST
IN THE SUNLIGHT,
I SAW HIS FACE...
AND TO MY UTTER HORROR,
THE DEMON WAS MY FATHER.
THE CREWLESS SHIP DRIFTED AWAY
WITH THE MASK STILL ABOARD.
I HAD SURVIVED,
BUT IT WAS COLD COMFORT,
KNOWING THE MASK'S DREADFUL
POWER COULD BE UNLEASHED AGAIN.
I DEDICATED MY LIFE TO FINDING
A WAY TO STOP ITS EVIL.
THAT PLEDGE LED
TO MY DISCOVERY OF HAMON.
THE ENERGY WE CALL HAMON
IS CREATED BY THE FLOW
OF ONE'S BLOOD.
THOSE WHO WEAR THE MASK
FEED ON THE BLOOD OF OTHERS
TO CONSUME THAT ENERGY.
HAMON AND THE MASK, THEY ARE
TWO SIDES OF THE SAME COIN.
JoJo: OF COURSE.
WE CAN OVERLOAD DIO
WITH THAT WHICH ANIMATES HIM.
Zeppeli: CORRECT. IF WE CAN HIT
DIO WITH ENOUGH HAMON ENERGY,
THAT DEVIL WILL BURST ASUNDER.
HAMON'S RIPPLES
ARE THE SAME FORM
AS THE WAVES OF LIGHT
SENT OUT BY THE SUN ITSELF,
THE BANE OF ALL VAMPIRES.
JoJo: BARON ZEPPELI,
I BEG OF YOU,
TEACH ME HOW TO WIELD IT.
I PROMISE I'LL GIVE IT MY ALL.
Zeppeli: YOU DON'T GET A CHOICE
IN THE MATTER, AMICO.
GIVEN YOUR CONTENTIOUS HISTORY
WITH DIO,
I'M SURE
HE WILL BE COMING FOR YOU.
( laughs )
♪
THERE IS A POETRY TO THIS, JOJO.
BREATHING OXYGENATES YOUR BLOOD.
YOUR BLOOD CARRIES THE OXYGEN
THROUGHOUT YOUR BODY.
IT ENRICHES THE CELLS,
GIVING THEM
THE POWER TO KEEP ON LIVING.
THOSE CELLS COMBINE TO FORM YOU.
LIKE RIPPLES IN THE WATER,
YOUR BODY THRUMS WITH THE HAMON
CREATED BY PROPER BREATHING.
ALL THAT IS LEFT IS TO USE IT!
( JoJo grunts )
THERE'S NO WAY HE COULD HAVE
REACHED ME FROM THERE.
HOW DID HE DO THAT?
Zeppeli: ZOOM PUNCH
IS A USEFUL ONE.
I MERELY DISLOCATED MY SHOULDER.
HAMON DULLS THE PAIN,
AND THE SURPRISE
IS WELL WORTH THE EFFORT.
YOU MUST MAINTAIN
THE RHYTHM OF YOUR BREATH,
EVEN WHEN TAKING A HIT.
IF YOUR MIND OR HEART
ARE TEMPESTUOUS,
THE CALIBER OF YOUR HAMON
WILL SUFFER.
‐ JoJo: YES, SIR.
‐ Speedwagon: OI!
I FOUND SOMETHING!
JoJo: EH? SPEEDWAGON.
SO THE VILLAGE
IS CALLED WIND KNIGHTS LOT?
Speedwagon: RIGHT.
THEY'VE HAD A STRING
OF DISAPPEARANCES LATELY,
PEOPLE VANISHING AFTER DARK,
AND FOLKS HAVE CAUGHT GLIMPSES
OF A FELLA WHO LOOKS LIKE DIO.
Zeppeli: WE'RE OUT OF TIME NOW.
YOUR FINAL TEST WILL BE ONE
OF LIFE OR DEATH, MY PUPIL.
JoJo: YES, SIR. I'LL MEET HIM
IN COMBAT AND LAY HIM LOW.
Speedwagon: GIVE HIM HELL.
LOOK, GENTS.
THE ENTRANCE
TO WIND KNIGHTS LOT.
JoJo: WE'LL ATTACK DIO
WHILE THERE'S STILL PLENTY
OF LIGHT LEFT IN THE SKY.
♪
ERINA. I LEFT WITHOUT
GIVING YOU A PROPER FAREWELL.
I SWEAR I WILL RETURN TO HER.
( thump )
Speedwagon: HUH?
JoJo: WHY DID WE STOP?
Speedwagon: OI, MATE!
HURRY IT UP!
JoJo: KEEP AN EYE OUT.
SUNLIGHT CAN'T PROTECT US
IN HERE.
Zeppeli: WELL? WHAT'S WRONG?
( Speedwagon gasps )
( screams )
♪
JoJo: IS IT DIO?
IT HAS TO BE HIM.
Zeppeli: LISTEN, BOTH OF YOU.
STEP AWAY FROM THE HORSES.
( Jack growling )
( Speedwagon gasps )
WHAT IN THE BLUE HELL?!
THAT CRAZY BLIGHTER'S
INSIDE OUR HORSE!
GOOD GOD,
THIS ONE'S MAD AS A HATTER!
DIO'S EVIL, YEAH,
BUT I AIN'T SEEN HIM
JUMP OUT OF ANY ANIMALS SO FAR.
JoJo: HE MUST BE
GATHERING MINIONS,
AND WHO KNOWS
HOW MANY HE MIGHT HAVE?
( Zeppeli sighs )
STAND ASIDE, MY YOUNG FRIENDS.
I WILL DO THE FIGHTING.
( Jack growls )
Zeppeli: HE IS A ZOMBIE.
THEY MUST FEED
ON LIVING FLESH TO SURVIVE.
HOWEVER, THEY ARE IN CONSTANT
THRALL TO THEIR MASTER,
NOT UNLIKE MARIONETTES.
Jack: OH, YOU LADS IS BOTH
AS WHITE AS A SHEET.
ALL THE BLOOD IS
DRAINED FROM YOUR FACES.
MAYBE I SHOULD CUT OFF
THOSE USELESS HEADS OF YOURS
AND WATCH IT SPRAY
OUTTA YOUR NECKS.
( both gasp )
Jack: NOW,
YOU MEWLING CORPSES‐TO‐BE,
PREPARE FOR THE CARNAGE!
Zeppeli: TELL ME,
WHAT'S HIS NEXT MOVE?
YOU MUST THINK AS HE DOES.
JOJO, THIS STRATEGY
WILL SERVE YOU IN GOOD STEAD.
ASK YOURSELF, "WHAT WOULD BE
THE MOST ADVANTAGEOUS THING
FOR MY FOE TO DO NEXT?"
HIM, FOR EXAMPLE.
IF HE BLOCKS OFF
THE TUNNEL ENTRANCE,
WE CAN'T RETREAT
TO THE SUNLIGHT.
( Jack growls )
( both gasp )
Zeppeli: JUST AS I PREDICTED,
HE'S BLOCKED OUR RETREAT!
JoJo: SPEEDWAGON, JUMP!
Zeppeli: TRY HARDER.
( Jack growling )
( JoJo gasps )
KNIVES ARE COMING OUT OF HIM.
Speedwagon: BARON ZEPPELI,
YOU DIDN'T SAY NOTHING
ABOUT FIGHTING A PINCUSHION.
♪
( Jack roars )
Zeppeli: HAMON CUTTER!
HAH HAH HAH HAH!
Jack: EH?
Zeppeli: I'M AFRAID YOUR BLADES
ARE RATHER DULL
COMPARED TO MY HAMON CUTTER.
JOJO, THIS CREATURE
ILLUSTRATES A PRINCIPLE.
IMAGINE A MINUSCULE FLEA,
SO SMALL THAT IT'S
BARELY VISIBLE.
WHY IS IT THEY BITE HUMANS
WHO TOWER OVER THEM
WITHOUT A SINGLE THOUGHT
TO THEIR OWN SAFETY?
WOULD YOU CALL
THEIR BEHAVIOR COURAGEOUS?
OF COURSE NOT.
IT'S HUNGER COMPELLING THEM.
I WILL TELL YOU
WHAT COURAGE IS, JOJO.
COURAGE IS TO LOOK
YOUR FEAR IN THE EYE
AND KNOW THAT IT HAS
NO DOMINION OVER YOU!
FEAR SCATTERS YOUR BREATHING.
WHEN YOU TOSS YOUR FEAR
INTO THE DUST,
BREATHING IS THE SWORD
EVER AT YOUR HIP.
BREATHE WITH COURAGE, AND YOU
WILL NEVER WANT FOR HAMON.
BRAVERY IS
OUR BIRTHRIGHT, LADS!
AND FOR ALL THE ABILITIES
THEY MAY BRING INTO A BATTLE,
COURAGE IS SOMETHING
A ZOMBIE RELINQUISHED
WHEN HE TOOK THIS FORM!
THEY'RE NO BETTER THAN FLEAS!
SENDO WAVE KICK!
( both gasp )
Zeppeli: A KNEE FULL OF HAMON
TO THE HEAD
SEEMS TO HAVE CURED
THIS ONE'S BRAGGADOCIO.
Speedwagon: I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
HE DIDN'T EVEN SPILL ANY WINE.
Zeppeli: JOJO,
YOU FINISH THE CREATURE OFF.
DESTROY THE BRAIN.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
ANYTHING ELSE,
AND YOU RISK IT COMING BACK.
( Jack roars )
TIME FOR THE SLAUGHTER,
NAUGHTY LITTLE PIGS.
( wall rumbles )
I'LL CUT YOU TO SHREDS
ONE BY ONE.
Speedwagon: DON'T TELL ME
WE'RE FOLLOWING HIM
INTO THAT PASSAGEWAY.
Zeppeli: IT HAS TO BE DESTROYED,
BUT WE WILL BE DOING
NO SUCH THING.
‐ JOJO...
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
Zeppeli: I EXPECT YOU
TO FINISH OFF THIS ABOMINATION
WITHOUT SPILLING A SINGLE DROP.
ALL RIGHT, ONE LAST BIT
OF ADVICE BEFORE YOU GO.
THERE WERE NO VIKINGS
IN THE LAND OF NORWAY
UNTIL THE NORTH WIND
BLEW IN AND CREATED THEM.
IF EVEN ONE DROP OF THAT VINO
GOES TO WASTE,
I DON'T CARE HOW UTTERLY
YOU DEFEAT THE ZOMBIE.
I WILL ABANDON YOU HERE AND NOW.
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ Speedwagon: OI!
LISTEN TO YOURSELF.
HAVE YOU GONE INSANE?
Zeppeli: I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING!
I WILL DO MY BEST.
LIKE THE VIKINGS, I WILL BE
STRENGTHENED BY HARDSHIP.
( Speedwagon gasps )
( Zeppeli grunts )
JoJo: IT'S A LABYRINTH.
EVEN WITH THIS TORCH,
ALL IT'S DOING IS
CASTING SHADOWS TO BEDEVIL ME.
( footsteps echoing )
( gasps ) THE TORCH!
I'M BRIGHT AS DAY TO HIM!
( yells )
( gasps )
( Jack laughs )
JoJo: ALL THIS DOES
IS ILLUMINATE MY POSITION,
BUT WITHOUT IT, I HAVEN'T
A CLUE WHERE HE'S LURKING
OR FROM WHERE HE'LL STRIKE.
Jack: EVEN IN THE DARK, I CAN
SMELL THE BLOOD FROM HIS ARM.
JoJo: I MUST THINK LIKE MY FOE,
JUST AS THE BARON COMMANDED.
I'M SURE HE'S CLOSE.
NEXT, I MUST MASTER MY FEAR,
LEST IT SAP MY HAMON.
BREATHING IS
THE SWORD AT MY HIP.
Jack: THAT'S IT.
A LITTLE CLOSER,
AND I'LL BE PICKING MY TEETH
WITH YOUR BONES, BOY.
Zeppeli: THE HARSH WIND BLOWING
DOWN OFF OF THE ARCTIC OCEAN
BIRTHED THE FEARSOME VIKINGS.
ONLY WHEN WE ARE TOSSED HEADLONG
INTO THE CRUCIBLE OF ADVERSITY
DO WE RISE TO THE CHALLENGE.
WHAT WILL A GLASS OF VINO
CREATE THIS NIGHT?
IF HE SHOULD FAIL,
DIO HAS ALREADY WON.
JoJo: WHAT?
THE WINE IS RIPPLING.
OF COURSE. JUST LIKE WHEN WE
WERE TRAINING IN THE STREAM.
IT'S CONDUCTING THE HAMON.
IT PASSES
THROUGH THE GLASS, MY ARM,
MY BODY, THE GROUND ITSELF!
I CAN FEEL HIS VIBRATIONS
IN THE WINE.
WITH HAMON,
ALL IS MADE CLEAR TO ME NOW.
MY SPIRIT TREMBLES!
MY HEART IS ABLAZE!
I'VE FOUND YOU, ZOMBIE!
THESE STONES
OFFER NO PROTECTION!
SENDO HAMON OVERDRIVE!
Jack: TURN THE CORNER
SO I CAN FEAST ON YOU.
( screams )
Zeppeli: SOUNDS LIKE
YOU PASSED THE TEST
WITH FLYING COLORS, JOJO.
EXCELLENT.
ADVERSITY HAS
MADE THE LAD A VIKING.
( JoJo exhales )
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Zeppeli: THIS TIME, I BREAK YOU.
Men: CURSES ON YOU, QUEEN!
Speedwagon: CAN HE
OVERCOME THIS DELUSION?!
Man: A DUEL BETWEEN HEROES.
JoJo: I'M ENDING YOUR REIGN
OF TERROR HERE AND NOW!