[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball.
After Bulma
repaired Goku's radar,
the two raced off in search
of the third Dragon Ball.
They found it...
at the bottom of the ocean.
Determined to retrieve
what he hoped would be
his grandpa's four-star Ball,
Goku dived into
the mysterious unknown
with his lungs full of air
and his heart
filled with bravery.
Unfortunately, not even Goku
could hold his breath
long enough
to reach the ocean floor,
although he gave it
his best shot.
[groans lightly]
[NARRATOR] In the end,
Goku had to turn back.
But he wasn't discouraged.
He and Bulma
simply switched to plan B
and headed to Roshi's island,
in hopes that the old Master
would allow the explorers
to borrow his submarine.
I wish we didn't
have to involve Roshi.
There's no telling
what he'll ask in exchange.
But I bet he asks me.
Faster, Nimbus!
[BULMA screams]
Hey, flyboy! Slow down!
[stammers]
[BULMA] Hello! Goku!
Small girl hanging by your hair!
Sorry.
[chuckles nervously]
[GOKU] I think we're
almost there.
[laughs] I see it!
[GOKU] I see it! We're here!
[sighs]
[beeping]
[PILOT] This is Scout Zero
One to Command Center.
We have a situation.
Repeat, we have a situation.
We've located two downed
scout planes on a small island,
southwest of Base Seven.
[PILOT] Both pilots are wounded.
They were attacked by the boy.
There is one other thing, sir.
[BLUE groans]
[PILOT] The pilots claim
the boy wasn't traveling alone.
Apparently, he was
accompanied by a young woman.
This is General Blue.
What exactly
did the female look like?
[PILOT] That's all the
information we were able to get
before the pilots passed out.
[BLUE] I am talking
to a dead man right now
if I don't get a full report
on my desk in two hours.
Do you understand me?!
This boy has laid waste
to two of our best regiments
and I will not be the third.
He may possess some skill,
but there is one thing
that I know for certain,
and that is...
[BLUE] nothing lasts forever.
[laughs intensely]
[TURTLE grunts lightly]
Hm?
Hey! Hu-huh!
[laughs]
Oh, Goku!
This is certainly a surprise!
Welcome back.
It's good to see you again!
It's good to
see you, too, Turtle.
I sure have missed everybody.
It's been way too long.
Yeah. So, are you here
on business or pleasure?
I need Master Roshi's help.
Oh. Hang on, I'll get him...
Hey, Master! Master!
[TURTLE] Goku's here!
[music plays from TV]
[ROSHI groans lightly]
[laughing]
Aaah...! [continues laughing]
[TURTLE] Hey, Master!
I'm busty. I mean busy!
[ROSHI] Ah! Confound it!
Can't a fella get a
moment's peace around here?!
[TURTLE]
Goku's here to see you!
Mm?
Goku's here?
[GOKU laughs]
Oh! What brings
you out here, boy?
I thought you were off
looking for your Dragon Ball?
I still am!
And it's been loads of fun!
Uh, what can I help you with?
We need help... breathing...
I'd better let Bulma tell you.
[ROSHI] Bulma?
Eeeeh!
Eeeh!
Uuh!
[BULMA] Hello, Roshi.
Well I'll be a--how in
the world did you do that?!
See...? It's a
height-changing device
that can make someone
big or small.
Wha-ho!
Say now, that's something!
I know. Isn't it great?!
I programmed
the circuit relay to--
Bulma...
What about the thingy?
Oh yeah, that's right.
Say, Master Roshi,
Goku and I were curious as to
whether you might have
a submarine laying around here
that we could maybe borrow?
Why certainly.
What interest do you have
in a submarine?
We found another Dragon Ball
at the bottom of the ocean,
but it's way too deep
to swim to. I tried.
Is that right?
Okay, I'll lend it to you.
Thank you.
[BULMA] That was
just a little too easy.
However...
Nnnngh!
I'll need
that device in exchange.
My... microband?!
[ROSHI] Mhm. Mhm.
And that's it? Nothing else?
[ROSHI] Mhmmm.
Whew! That's a relief!
I was afraid you'd gotten
the wrong impression
during that incident
on Ox-King's mountain...
That really wasn't me...
[BULMA] I'm not the sort of
girl you're looking for.
Not that you're looking,
of course, at me.
--[GOKU] Hm?
--[BULMA chuckles nervously]
I'm going to
miss the micro-band,
but I know it's
for a good cause. Here.
Oh, yes!
Thank you, thank you!
Fine. Now hand over
the capsule for the submarine.
Patience,
my dear girl, patience.
Launch and Krillin
took it into town this morning
to do some shopping.
They should be back
any minute now. No biggie.
Let's see. I think
I'll take three onions,
two carrots,
and about three cucumbers.
Sure... Sure... No problem.
She's cute. Is she your sister?
[laughs]
[KRILLIN] No, no, no, no.
Hm...
[beeping]
[grunts]
[STAFF OFFICER] My guess is that
the boy is working with someone.
I don't pay you
to guess, now do I?
Your second-rate speculation
won't get me the Dragon Balls.
Mhmmm.
Tell me what we know!
[STAFF OFFICER] He knows
where the Dragon Ball is
and yet he's spending
a lot of time away from it.
Probably gathering supplies.
His radar is
quite sophisticated.
Not exactly something
you'd find in a boy's toy box.
He must be getting
assistance from someone.
[RED] That could mean
his headquarters is located
somewhere in that vicinity.
Yes, sir.
Well, don't just
stand there like a moron!
Contact General Blue
and have his scouts
find the kid's hideout.
I understand... Yes... Yes...
Right. I'll get
my men on it immediately.
[waves crashing]
Where are they?
Eh-heh. They'll be
back soon. Don't worry.
Turtle, what's taking
them so long?
I've got a bad feeling.
[LAUNCH] Ah, ah, ah, achoo!
Uh, uh, uh...
Don't talk
with food in your mouth!
[CLERK groans]
What kind of shop
doesn't sell green onions!
This is ridiculous! Come here!
[LAUNCH grunts]
[CLERK groans]
[KRILLIN]
Launch! Stop it! No! Stop it!
[LAUNCH] Get lost!
[KRILLIN yells]
[CROWD gasping]
Hey!
You want somethin'?!
--[LAUNCH] Here!
--[MAN] Aaah!
[growls]
[LAUNCH] What about the
rest of you?! You want some?!
[grunts]
[birds cawing]
[inhales]
Hey! Ready?!
Okay!
One!
[GOKU] Two! Three! Four! Five!
[yawning]
[ROSHI] Mm-hm-hm.
Can I get you something?
A-Another glass
of water perhaps?
No thanks.
I've had so many already
that I'm begining
to feel waterlogged.
That's a shame.
[ROSHI] It's about time!
Now go to the ladies' room
so I can use this micro-doo-dad!
That's enough. Bucket's full!
[chuckles]
Great job.
We'll eat well tonight!
Wait! Got one more!
[SMALL TURTLE groans]
Uh?
[SMALL TURTLE stammers]
Daddy!
Ooh! My son!
[BOTH laugh]
[BULMA groans]
[ROSHI] Ooh...
[BULMA]
I need to wash my hands.
[ROSHI] Sure... it's the first
door on your left, sweetie.
[ROSHI] Eeh...
Take your time!
Eeh... Heh... Heeehhh...
The longer the better!
[ROSHI] Boy, am I tired.
I think I'll go
lay down for a bit.
Ehhh... Uh...
[laughs intensely]
[ROSHI]
Calm down, Roshi, old boy!
You're going to
blow your shell. Heh.
Now let's see. I push these
two buttons and then, eh...
Presto! [chuckles]
[laughs]
[ROSHI panting]
Eureka!
[laughs]
[chuckles]
Good timing! Oh, yes!
Great timing! Heh-heh!
[laughs]
[ROSHI] You lucky devil!
This is worth
eighteen submarines!
[ROSHI chuckles]
Come on, mama,
let the good times roll!
[ROSHI] Eh?!
No...!
[grunts] No! Why?! Why would--
[ROSHI yells]
[splash]
[yells]
Huh. I could have
sworn I heard something.
[ROSHI groans, grunts]
[sniffs]
Pee-yew! That's worse
than Launch's stew!
Any word?
They're not here yet.
[ROSHI grunting]
[ROSHI] Hello.
Master, what happened to you?
Never mind!
But I thought
you went in to lie down.
How could you get all wet
if you were inside the house?
It's none of your business.
Be quiet, Turtle!
Hey everybody... Look, up there!
[BULMA] Huh?
It's about time they got back.
I could have been
faster than that.
They better have
a lot of groceries.
[GOKU] Hey guys!
[laughs]
Hi!
[chuckles] Goku!
[laughs]
I'm so glad to see you guys!
[GOKU laughs]
What a machine!
This sub is fantastic!
Hello... I-It's, uh, always
nice to see you again, Bloomer.
It's Bulma! Bul-ma!
We've been waiting for you.
Why are you so late?
Uh, well...
Launch had one of her episodes
while we were
at the market today.
Thought so.
[giggles]
Yeah, I sneezed again.
[chuckles]
Sounds like you two
had a big day!
Hey, Goku,
why are you here anyway?
This is Command Center
calling Scout 45.
[BLUE] Come in. What is
your P.L.C. status? Over.
This is Scout Zero One.
No sign of any base
in this sector.
However, there aren't too many
islands in this region,
so I anticipate Positive
Location Confirmation
to be imminent.
[BLUE] Roger that.
[PILOT] Over.
Uh-huh. Judging by this map,
you're definitely
going to need a submarine.
[humming]
[ROSHI clears throat]
You've been working
pretty hard, Launch.
Maybe you should
take a nice hot shower.
Hm! Sounds nice,
but I have to make dinner.
I'll take one later.
Okay. Darn it!
[KRILLIN] And I think... Yes,
if it really is around here,
you should be able to
find the pirate's treasure
easily with the submarine.
Pirate's?
Treasure?!
Did you say treasure?!
[ROSHI] Eh, say, Bulma,
wouldn't you like
a nice glass of iced tea?
I'm not thirsty, thanks.
So go on. Give us
the scoop on this treasure.
Master Roshi
knows more than I do.
What's that?
You know, the story
you always tell me.
The legend of
the missing pirate's treasure.
[ROSHI] Hm?
Oh yeah.
The pirate's treasure.
Long ago, these waters
were infested with
pirates who pillaged and
plundered everything in sight.
Not the sort you'd
invite over for fruit punch,
I'll tell you that...
[PIRATES yelling]
[ROSHI] Pirate ships were
heavily populated and armed.
Many royal vessels, carrying
precious jewels and riches,
fell prey to their attacks.
[ROSHI] Legend has it,
much of the stolen bounty
ended up on the ocean floor,
and is still there today.
[ROSHI] Yes, sir.
Whomever finds that treasure
is going to be
as rich as a king.
Mmm... How romantic.
We have to find this treasure.
I mean, we just have to.
Yeah, it sounds awesome,
doesn't it?
I'd love to
go with you and help.
Really? We could
sure use another person.
Can I go, Master? Please!
I know this map
like the back of my hand!
Mhm. I suppose...
But finish your chores first.
Yes sir!
[GOKU] Thanks, Master Roshi!
See you later!
--[ROSHI] Good luck, kiddos!
--[TURTLE] Bye! Take care!
There's something
I don't understand.
If we want
to go under the water,
then how come
we're in an airplane?
This baby does both.
It's a submarine
and an airplane.
Wow! An air fish!
The proper name is actually--
Oh no, I left
my rucksack at Roshi's
with the Dragon Balls inside!
It's okay. Relax.
Nothing's going to happen to it
while it's at
Master Roshi's house.
You're right. I'm just
being silly. What a relief!
[PILOT] Huh?
Priority message
for General Blue,
this is Scout Zero One.
I've spotted an
unidentified flying object
heading North, Northwest.
Would you like me
to follow in pursuit? Over.
[BLUE] Negative.
Backtrack its flight pattern.
If it is the boy, his base
can't be too far away. Over.
Copy that.
I've got something!
There's a house
on a small island.
Grid marking ESA Seven, zero,
two, four, niner, point. Over.
Go to visual tracking,
infrared scan.
Is anybody out there? Over.
[PILOT] Affirmative...
I have visual confirmation.
Repeat, I have visual
confirmation of an old man,
one woman, and a turtle.
All are outside the house
and appear to be unarmed.
Awaiting further
instructions. Over.
Ooh...
It sure is hot out here.
Maybe you should
take that shower now.
Huh?
[TURTLE] Oh brother.
The old man
must be the scientist
who designed the kid's radar.
[ROSHI laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Now that the Red Ribbon Army
knows about Roshi's island,
what will become
of Goku and his friends?
Find out next time, on another
exciting episode of Dragon Ball!