[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Fortuneteller Baba told Goku
and ChiChi of a magical furnace
that could extinguish
the mysterious flames
surrounding the
Ox King's castle.
Desperate, the brave pair
set out on their new quest,
which led them to the
treacherous Mount Five Elements.
After navigating their way
through perilous terrain
and lethal obstacles,
Goku and his fianceé
finally locate the magical
furnace and much more.
[GOKU]
I... guess we found it.
[NARRATOR]
Goku was shocked to find
his deceased grandfather, Gohan.
The young hero's
surprise turned to dismay
upon learning Gohan
now served the caretaker
of the magical furnace.
Despite their urgent pleas,
Annin was unwilling to
shut down the raging furnace.
[ANNIN] In theory, if the
magical fire were extinguished,
the plains of existence would
be thrown into utter chaos.
Actually, it sounds like fun.
Annin, please!
You must help.
Grandpa!
[GOHAN grunts]
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
I'm sorry. The flames cannot
be put out, for you, or anyone.
Now, think about it.
You wouldn't want
to be responsible
for the world's greatest
disaster, would you?
[NARRATOR]
And now, the conclusion.
[whimpering]
[groans]
Do your worst flames!
Rise as high as you wish.
I will not meet defeat
before I see my daughter
in her wedding dress!
I will keep it safe...
no matter what!
[GOKU] You can't ignore this.
Unless the fire is put out,
it will destroy the Ox King!
[CHICHI] I beg you!
Please save my father.
[GOHAN]
Hmm.
Annin?
Gohan, please...think
about what you're asking.
You would have me
sacrifice this entire world
to save but one life?
I guess I'm just not as
ready to give up yet!
[GOHAN] Goku, that's enough!
Watch your mouth!
[ANNIN]
Mhm... mhm.
Fine, I'll do it myself! Now
tell me how to put out the fire!
These noodles are delicious.
Here, try some.
I'm not hungry!
[BOTH gasp]
[growls]
[GOHAN]
Goku, that was extremely rude!
Annin, he begs for
your forgiveness.
I'm so sorry.
ChiChi, you don't have
to apologize.
[grunts]
What was that for?!
Goku, stop!
Your gums are showing.
Are you this rude to everyone,
or just to the people from
whom you're seeking help?
If you wanna put
out the fire so badly,
I suggest you turn
that handle over there.
Turn to the right.
Annin, please!
--[CHICHI] Wait!
--[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN]
Goku... wait! Stop it!
Goku!
Grandpa, let go!
No, I won't let you do this!
If the flames go out,
something terrible will happen!
I have to do this, Grandpa!
You don't know what
you're doing!
Let go!
[GOHAN yells]
[ANNIN]
Gohan!
[yelling]
[ANNIN grunts]
[ANNIN]
Let me give you a lift.
Enjoy the furnace!
Goku!
[GOKU yelling]
[groaning]
[CHICHI]
Are you all right?
Nice trip? Did you get
a good look at the steam
coming up from the furnace?
Yeah.
That steam turns into fog,
which covers the top of
Mt. Five Elements.
That fog is what I believe
to be the problem.
Uh? Fog?
That's right, dear. Fire
makes steam, steam becomes fog.
Take away the fire,
and surprise, no more fog.
What's so... bad about that?
Calm down and listen.
The fog is the only way
in and out of the path
that runs between
this world and the next.
When a person's life is over,
they pass into the Other World.
However, on the date
of their passing,
or during a special festival,
they can return to this world
and meet their descendants.
This journey can only take
place through the fog.
Without it, the gateway
would be sealed forever.
Losing the fog would not
only inhibit spirits
from traveling to this world,
but those that are already here
would be trapped
for all eternity.
That would include
the evil ones.
Eventually, the dark spirits
would overrun the Earth
and destroy everything.
[ANNIN]
This is not just a theory.
It will come to pass...
...should I allow you
to turn off the furnace.
What if the furnace were only
turned off for a short time?
Long enough to put out the
fire around my father's castle,
but without dissipating
the fog completely?
Won't work.
What do you mean?
Because, if the magical
fire goes out just once,
it would take 200
years to re-ignite.
In the meantime, this world
would grow cold and dark.
Evil would take hold,
and I can promise you,
it won't give up its
stranglehold for tender mercy!
[gasps]
Isn't there any way
to put out the fire
that threatens my father?
Please! I beg of you.
Don't let my father die!
[ANNIN]
There is a way, but...
[BOTH]
Really?
Hmm.
[yelling]
[gasps, grunting]
[gasps]
[grunting]
Round two!
[yelling]
Huh?
--[GOKU grunts]
--[ANNIN] Ah.
[grunting]
[ANNIN gasps]
[groaning]
Oh, Annin!
Goku, how could you be
so disrespectful?
This lady is Tajoro!
She has been the caretaker
of the magical furnace
for over ten thousand years!
[GOKU gasps]
Ten thousand years?
You're not old! You're ancient.
[growls]
Child! How dare you insult me!
You're in my world now!
[growls]
[gasp]
[screams]
[VILLAGERS]
Sire! Abandon the castle! Hurry!
Sire! Hurry! Get out!
Save yourself!
What's taking Goku so long?
Very soon, there won't be
any king or kingdom to save.
[panting]
Oh... the villagers.
I'm okay! I'm right here!
[chuckles]
--[VILLAGERS yelling]
--[VILLAGER A] Wait!
I see him there!
[VILLAGERS] Three cheers
for the Ox King! Hip-hip-hooray!
[BABA thinking]
He's tough. I'll give him that.
But this is a question of time,
and his is running out.
What is Goku doing?
[gasps]
[grunting]
[yells]
[ANNIN, GOKU grunt]
--[GOKU yells]
--[ANNIN grunts]
[grunting]
[ANNIN, GOKU grunt]
--[ANNIN grunts]
--[GOKU yelps]
Stay still!
[GOKU yelling]
Goku!
Well, if you think that's
something, try this!
N-No, it can't be!
[GOKU yells]
[screams, grunting]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU laughs]
--[GOKU] Uh?
--[CHICHI yelps]
The Bansho Fan!
That's right.
Should I wave it again?
Goku, no!
Listen, I think I know of
a way to save your father
without extinguishing the fire!
[sighs, giggles]
--Goku!
--[GOKU grunts]
[CHICHI laughs]
The Bansho Fan cannot
put out the fire alone.
We need something
to fill the hole
in the bottom of the furnace.
What do you need?
Tell me and I'll go get it.
Be warned. What I need
won't be that easy to get.
Don't worry. I can handle it.
What is it?
The bottom of the
furnace is made
of the octagon-shaped eggshells
from the fire-eater bird.
[BOTH]
Fire-eater bird?
Not only do we need egg
shells to fill in the hole,
but we need honey
from bees that live
in octagon-shaped honeycombs
to hold the shells in place.
[BOTH gasp]
--Well...
--Uh. Wait!
I have what we need.
ChiChi, you're incredible!
You have both of them?
Will these do?
Good enough, dear.
--[GOKU laughs]
--Goku.
[ANNIN]
Save your happiness.
[BOTH]
Uh?
The chance that our
plan will actually succeed
is slim to say the least.
I do not plan on failing.
[ANNIN]
The only thing that is certain,
is if you fail, you will die.
We must try. Go on.
Hmm.
Goku, in ten thousand years
I've never met as brave
a heart as yours.
Very well.
I will lift the pot,
while you go into the
furnace and fill the hole.
[GOKU]
Okay, let's do it.
[GOHAN]
Annin, I beg you to reconsider.
You know as well as I
that inside the furnace
is the sea of fire. Not even
Goku could survive in there.
This plan is folly.
But your grandson
has the Bansho Fan.
[GOHAN]
I understand.
Listen. You have a chance,
but the danger is immeasurable.
From over the furnace,
you must wave the fan once.
This will part the flames
and create a path.
Follow along this path
until you reach the hole,
fill it in, and get out. The
time allowed for all of this is
as short as the
blink of an eye.
Goku, the rest of your
life hinges on this moment.
I will succeed.
Goku, the furnace is gigantic.
It's as large as a
mountain on the inside.
Are you sure you're up
to this task? Are you ready?
Hmm.
[panting]
[OX KING thinking] ChiChi
will make a beautiful bride.
[panting]
[OX KING thinking] I would have
loved to see my little girl
in her mother's dress.
[panting]
Gook luck, Goku, my boy.
Please be careful!
Goku, Gohan's description of
the furnace is not exaggerated.
However, the furnace is
even more ancient than I am.
Should some chemical
flowing from the pot
have eroded more than one hole,
you will not have enough
supplies to fix the damage.
Hmm.
[VILLAGERS chatter]
[BABA]
Ox King, can you hear me?
Answer my call
if you're still alive.
[OX KING panting]
ChiChi.
Good or bad, this will
all be over in a moment.
[grunts]
[grunting]
[GOKU]
Heyah!
[GOKU grunts]
Ah!
[ANNIN grunting]
I've reached the bottom!
[grunts]
Uh?
[grunting]
[GOKU]
Where is it?
Goku.
[whimpers]
[BABA]
Ox King.
Are you there?
[laughs]
That's it!
[grunts]
[VILLAGERS chatter]
Goku, please!
Time is running out!
[GOKU]
I'm coming, ChiChi!
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
[GOKU thinking] Uh oh,
not much time left. Focus!
[whimpering]
[groaning]
Gohan, we don't
have any more time!
[groaning]
[growling]
Bad news. I'm
running out of time.
Uh?
[grunts]
Power Pole, extend!
Come on, work!
I have to make it!
[ANNIN groaning]
[ANNIN thinking] If he's not
back by now, he's finished.
[groans]
[CHICHI thinking]
Goku, please.
[GOKU yells]
[gasp]
He made it!
[GOHAN chuckles]
[CHICHI squeals, laughs]
You made it back in one piece!
You're safe now!
How did it go?
Did you fix the furnace?
Mm-hm.
[CHICHI laughs]
[grunts]
Well done, Goku.
As the caretaker of the furnace,
I would like to extend
my deepest gratitude.
[CHICHI sighs]
This is the first job
you've completed as a couple.
Judging by its success, you
should be very happy together.
--[CHICHI sighs]
--Hm. You too, Grandpa.
--[CHICHI laughs]
--Have a happy life with Annin.
[laughs]
Well...
[VILLAGERS chatter]
[BABA thinking] I'd hate to
be on the clean-up crew.
[gasp]
Ohh no, Ox King!
[yelps]
[OX KING groans]
[chuckles]
I saved it! The dress
didn't get a scratch!
[chuckles]
[OX KING grunts]
You scared me!
[OX KING laughing]
[CHICHI]
Father!
[OX KING]
Oh?
ChiChi! Goku!
Something good did come of this.
I think I got a tan!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
--[OX KING sobbing]
--[GOKU laughing]
Thank you!
Thank you all for joining us
on this day I've been
waiting for my whole life.
I'm so glad my father's
here to see it.
You look... beautiful.
Your mother would be so proud.
You were right about
this dress. It's perfect.
I can't imagine
this day without it.
[CHICHI laughs]
Goku, welcome to the family.
--[CHICHI sighs]
--[GOKU] Hm.
--[CHICHI giggles]
--[GOKU gasps]
[BOTH laugh]
[NARRATOR] Goku and
ChiChi's wedding ceremony
ends in joyful bliss
for one and all.
But what future lies ahead
for the newlyweds?
[BABA] The future? Well, it
couldn't hurt to take a peek!
Mm... mmm... mm.
Ohh.
[NARRATOR]
For the further adventures
of Goku and his friends,
be sure to watch Dragon Ball Z!