Just like you, Doctor...
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball...
Murasaki threatened
Dr. Flappe into helping him
steal Goku's Dragon Balls.
But little Suno's
big lungs brought Number 8
crashing in to scare
the purple thief away.
[GOKU] Ha...!
[NARRATOR] Murasaki tried to
flee across the frozen hillside,
until Goku's Kamehameha Wave
placed him directly in the
path of an icy avalanche.
[MURASAKI screams]
[NARRATOR] Later, Dr. Flappe
was able to disarm the bomb
inside Android Number 8,
much to everyone's relief.
But when it came to
fixing the Dragon Radar,
the doctor had little luck,
and Goku will have
to look elsewhere.
[VOICES chattering, laughing]
Congratulations, Eighter.
Thanks!
You'll stay with me now.
I'm so glad.
I am too.
Can't you stay?
Do you have to go
find your Dragon Ball?
That Dragon Ball is all I have
left to remember my Grandpa by.
Sleep here tonight, it's much
too late to begin a trip.
Okay!
[SUNO] It's a slumber party!
[SUNO &amp; GOKU laugh]
Well, since you have
to bid farewell
to your friend Goku tomorrow,
why don't you go ahead and
stay here with him tonight?
So, then, I'll
see you later then?
Yes!
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Come to my
house in the morning, Eighter.
Good night, everyone!
[ALL] Goodbye! See ya later!
See you soon! Bye!
Still doesn't work...
What will you do without
your Dragon radar?
How will you find the ball?
I'll just go to Bulma's
house and get it fixed.
[NUMBER 8] Huh?
Who's that?
She's the one who
gave this to me.
She made it.
I see.
Where is this "Bulma?"
Maybe you know the way...
She lives in some place
called "West City."
[SUNO] Hmm...
West City...
I think...
Uhhhm... That way!
I've heard of it.
It's far, how will
you get there?
I'm gonna walk.
What?! You're walking?
I guess there's no
other way, though.
There's not a single plane
or car in the whole village.
Too bad!
Well, I'll pack
you a huge lunch.
Really?!
I just know you
can make it there!
[SUNO] You have a
big day tomorrow,
so let's get some
sleep. Good night!
[GOKU] Good night!
[NUMBER 8] Good night!
[GOKU snores]
I've never slept with
a blanket before.
It's cozy!
[ROOSTER crows]
[SNOW MOLES squeak]
[SUNO'S DAD] What?!
Oh, you're going on foot there?
Mm-hmm!
My Flying Nimbus
got blown up.
Huh?!
Flying Nimbus you say...?
Son, you once had
a Nimbus cloud?
[SUNO'S DAD] Nimbus Cloud?
Yeah... I did.
How do you know about
the Flying Nimbus?
Well, you see...
When I was a young boy,
there were several of those
things around these parts...
w-weren't there?
Oh, why, yes indeed!
Yes, now, there used to be many
Nimbuses floating around here.
But since only those pure of
heart can ride them,
and they're getting pretty rare,
the clouds have nearly
disappeared now.
[VILLAGE CHIEF chuckles]
If you can ride one,
you must be a very good person.
Thank you.
But my Flying Nimbus is broken!
[ELDER laughs]
A Flying Nimbus
can't be destroyed.
Have you tried calling for it?
[GOKU] Uh-uh.
No, I haven't.
I thought it was gone for good.
Well, then, call it now!
Alright!
Fly-ing Niiiiim-buuus!
Coooome to meee!
Flying Nimbus!
Nothing's happening
Give it time.
[GOKU] Huh...?
Heh, heh. Hey!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[GOKU laughs]
My nimbus!
It's back!
[gasping]
[ELDER &amp; VILLAGE CHIEF laugh]
Nimbus! I thought
I'd never see you again!
I'm so happy you're here!
I missed you so much!
I can't believe you're back!
We'll have so much fun together!
You'll see!
[GOKU laughs]
[ELDER] He can really
ride that thing...
Well, I'm off!
Take care, everyone!
Thank you for everything, Goku.
You're my very best friend!
Don't forget!
Never let those Red Ribbon
guys get you down!
I never let anything
get me down.
I'm really going to
miss all of you guys!
Now, off to West City!
Go, Nimbus, go!
[SUNO] Goku!
[SUNO] West is that way!
Oh, yeah... Ha, ha...
[GOKU] See ya!
[SUNO]
That Nimbus Cloud is so...
[NUMBER 8]
Amazing!
Goodbye, my good friend!
Watch out for trees!
[VILLAGERS] Bye, Goku!
I'll miss you! Bye! Goodbye!
[GOKU] Wheeee!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Hey, Nimbus,
there's a rainbow chasing us!
[GOKU laughs]
It's so much warmer
up here already!
[NARRATOR] Having been
reunited with his old friend,
the Flying Nimbus,
Goku once again embarks
on his journey into the unknown.
And over every
mountain he passes,
over every ocean he crosses,
Goku finds continual delight
in the simple wonders
of a world still
very new to him.
Whoa!
Look! We've got company, Nimbus!
[NARRATOR] But little does
our young hero realize,
his seemingly care-free journey
is fraught with danger--
As a sinister eye closely
follows his every move.
[beeping]
[STAFF OFFICER] The radar
shows the Dragon Balls
are traveling west.
And they're moving fast!
[growling]
[GOKU] Wow, it's like
a maze down there!
[CROWD murmuring,
horns honking]
Whoa...
So, this is the city?!
Bulma actually lives here?!
[CROWD chattering]
Thanks, Nimbus. I'll walk now.
This place is awfully
crowded, and noisy too!
[brakes squeal]
[GOKU gasps]
Brat! Open your eyes!
Watch out!
Um, excuse me,
but where does Bulma live?
I've been looking all over.
Well, how should I know?!
[horns honking]
[DRIVERS yelling]
Now get out of the road
or you'll be flattened!
[GOKU] Why are they
in such a rush?
[GOKU] Ma'am,
where is Bulma's house?
Who? "Bulma"?
Yeah, Bulma.
I have no idea.
Why don't you go bother
someone else, okay?
[GOKU] Don't you know her?
You live in the same town!
What now...?
Maybe I should stop
someone else and ask them?
Hey, over here!
Hi. Get in.
Well?
Oh! You'll take me to Bulma's?
Great!
Thank you!
It's really nice of you
to give me a ride like this!
Yeah, where we goin'?
To Bulma's house, please!
[TAXI DRIVER] I got that,
but where is it?
I don't know yet...
Been searching, though.
[brakes squealing]
Hey, buddy, you got
any money to pay
for this little
excursion of yours?!
[GOKU] Money?
No, I don't have any.
[TAXI DRIVER screams]
What was youse thinkin'?!
Youse got no cash,
youse got no lift!
Jerk!
Wh-What...?
I have to pay to find out
where she lives in this city?
Oh, great.
How am I supposed
to find some money?
[CROWD murmuring]
[GOKU] What's going on in there?
[murmuring continues]
[GOKU] Pardon me...
Excuse me.
Huh...?
[knuckles cracking]
[CAMO GUYS cheering]
[CROWD murmuring]
Ready?
Hooo!
Hah!
Ho-ha!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[growling]
[CROWD cheers, groans]
Wow!
[applause, cheering]
Well, who's next then?
Take me down for a
hundred thousand zeni!
Which one of you's got the guts?
Come on! Step up!
So, how about it, men?
Any of you think
you can beat me?
If you can make me give up,
the dough is yours...
No tricks, this is for real!
Hey! That's the answer!
I'll win the money,
like it's a tournament.
So, why don't you try?
You've got
to be kidding.
He's a master of kickboxing,
and I hear he's undefeated.
I want to fight!
[CROWD] Huh?!
Huh...?
Hey! I said I'll fight!
--[CROWD laughs]
--Gimme a second!
[laughing continues]
No joke?
Are you serious?
[CROWD laughs]
Yeah. I could sure
use the money.
[CROWD laughs]
You're really
gonna take me on?
Uh-huh, as long as I really
get the money when I win!
[CROWD laughs]
Phew!
Okay, the zeni is
yours if you beat me.
I usually charge
an entrance fee,
but for a challenger
of your caliber,
I'd be honored to
fight you for free.
Thank you!
I promise I won't hurt you bad.
[CROWD laughs]
FIGHTER] O-kay!
[laughter continues]
[GOKU] Ready!
Then let's get
it started now.
So, me first?
Sure, sure!
Huh...?
[GOKU yells]
[FIGHTER groans]
[CROWD gasps]
[coughing, squealing]
See anything?
Uh-uh.
[GOKU] Give up?
[CROWD gasping]
[FIGHTER laughs]
No way! We were
just getting started.
--[CROWD laughs]
--Okay...
[laughing continues]
I know your secret,
you've studied
a little martial arts,
haven't you, kid?
Yes, I've had some training.
A-ha, I just knew it!
[GOKU] Ready for another round?
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[CROWD gasps]
[FIGHTER whimpers]
I think you should probably
go ahead and give up now.
[FIGHTER growls]
You little nitwit!
[GOKU] Whoa!
Missed me!
Almost!
[FIGHTER yells]
Huh?!
[GOKU chuckles]
Here I come!
[FIGHTER squeals]
[CROWD gasps]
[FIGHTER whimpers]
[CROWD murmurs]
[whimpering continues]
I... surrender!
I got money!
[CROWD gasping,
murmuring]
[gasping]
[FIGHTER sighs]
I'll sure find her now!
[GOKU] Who can I
ask for directions?
Hey...
Check out what
the kid's packin'.
[GOKU] Uhh...
Yeah! We just hit the jackpot!
[THUG] Hey, uh, kid.
C'mere for a second.
[GOKU] Uhh...
Huh?
I got a little question for ya!
[GOKU] What is it?
Step into my office.
[GOKU chuckles]
What do you want?
[PIG GUY chuckles]
[THUG chuckles]
Whatever you have!
Hand it over!
Hey, sir?
Do you know where Bulma lives?
This idn't no time
for questions!
Give me that cash!
No, it's mine!
[GOKU raspberries]
[GOKU giggles]
Now are you gonna tell me
where Bulma's house or not?
Argh!
Stupid kid, do you
want me to hurt you?!
[PIG GUY grunts]
Uhhh...
That's it!
[THUG grunts]
[THUG laughs]
Yeah, okay!
B-B-Bulma's house...
Yeah, uh, you should try
t-to find a police man.
Yeah, uh, an of-officer should
be able help you with that!
[THUG laughs]
Okay, I'll find
this guy "Police".
Thank you!
[GOKU laughs]
[THUG whimpers]
No problem...
Don't mention it...
Um, like, you're
looking for a policeman?
Um, I think there's
one right over there.
Ah! I see him! Thanks!
Here's some money.
Hey! Mr. Police!
Uhh...
You say "Bulma's"
her name, huh?
You don't happen to have
her home address, or...
a description perhaps?
Humm... Ah-ha!
Okay... blue hair... and-and
big eyes... talks a lot...
Put this over here...
okay, in the back...
--[POLICEMAN] Uh-huh...
--[GOKU giggles]
Ha-ha! This is her!
[GOKU laughs]
[POLICEMAN] Well, uh, that's
not quite enough to go on there.
Why not?
Well, "Bulma", that...
that's an interesting
name there...
There aren't too many
Bulmas out there.
Maybe I can find her in here.
I'm not really supposed to
doing this, but here goes, eh?
Okay, "Bulma"...
There's three of them.
Which one is your friend there?
Is it, uh, this one?
[GOKU laughs] That's not her!
[POLICEMAN] Okay, uh,
what about her?
[GOKU] Ah! That's her!
That's Bulma!
Ho-ho, golly!
That there's the daughter of the
Capsule Corporation's president!
Come on! Tell me!
Where does she live?
[POLICEMAN] It's kinda far away,
so I'll just give you a lift.
Hop on, eh?
But I'm all out of money...
What the--?!
I don't take bribes!
[GOKU] Uhh...
You weren't fooling me
about being a friend
of that there girl's
there, were ya?
No, I'm her friend!
[POLICEMAN]
That there's the place!
[GOKU] Here?
Oh, wow!
It's giant!
[GOKU laughs]
Bullllll-maaaa!
[NARRATOR] It's been a
new type of adventure
for Goku finding
Bulma in this big city.
But if she can fix
his Dragon Radar,
he'll soon be back to the
business he knows best!
Tune in next time,
as Goku continues his quest
for the seven magic
Dragon Balls!