[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
Goku charged into battle
against Krillin
for the sixth match in the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
[NARRATOR] Bulma and
the gang joined the crowd
in support of their friends.
Though not everyone was
a fan, namely Master Shen,
who blamed Goku for the death
of his brother, Mercenary Tao.
Punch after punch, the fighting
seemed to go on forever,
with neither opponent
gaining much ground.
[KRILLIN yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[KRILLIN groans]
[NARRATOR] Krillin
tried to grab the lead
with an assortment
of crafty tricks.
But Goku was ready for him,
thwarting his
friend's every scheme,
until all hope
of a quick victory
vanished before his eyes.
Krillin was dumbfounded
by Goku's maneuver,
as was the audience... mostly.
Goku's incredible speed
made him virtually invisible.
Allowing him to move closer...
and closer... and closer.
[GOKU]
Ah-la-la-la-la!
[NARRATOR] Krillin was
knocked from the ring
before he knew what hit him,
and Goku was on his way
to fight in
the championship round.
[SHEN] Enjoy this
small victory, Goku.
It will be your last!
[NARRATOR] And now,
Goku must battle Tien Shinhan
to see who will become the
new Master of Martial Arts.
[ANNOUNCER] Fight fans are
in a frenzy of anticipation
as the final match of the
22nd World Martial Arts
Tournament begins today.
Last tournament's
second place winner,
Goku, will take on the
volatile Tien Shinhan
in what promises to be
an exciting battle.
If you aren't here,
you should be!
[YAMCHA chuckles]
Good morning, Yamcha--
huh? Yamcha?
[NURSE]
How strange.
[CROWD chatter]
I tell you what, this fight's
gonna be bad to the bone.
We've been camping
here five months
waiting for this here match.
Yeah, I quit my job
for this fight.
But I don't care.
This is great.
Can it get more crowded?
This is ridiculous!
They should have more sense
than to make people
stand out here in this heat.
It's poor management.
They never hire enough people
to staff these events.
They try to save a few bucks
and we have to pay for it.
Personally, I don't
mind these fights,
as long as there's no violence.
What do they do? Is this
like a performance,
or do they totally
hit each other?
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ahhh...
[sneezes]
Hi! Today we're going to
work out our legs
with an emphasis
on flexibility.
[ROSHI]
Mmm!
Up, up, and up,
and up, and up...
[TRAINER] Up, feel
the burn. Up, and up...
[ROSHI] What's wrong
with the volume?
I can barely hear a thing!
You really shouldn't sit
so close to the television.
Oh, be quiet! How I choose to
ruin my eyes is my business!
Now if you don't mind, I'm
trying to work out here! Sheesh!
That doesn't look very fun...
[distant car horns honking]
[KRILLIN] All those
people must be here
to see you fight!
They've come from all over,
so don't let them down.
I promise to do my best.
Mm-hmm!
Special delivery!
For you.
Thanks! Wow, it feels warm!
Mm-ah!
That's because it
just came out of the dryer.
I hope it didn't
shrink too much.
I'm surprised it didn't melt.
The dryer had three settings:
hot, magma, and sun.
Nice... But how did you
keep the colors from fading?
Trade secret.
Hey, where's Oolong?
[BULMA]
Hm? Huh?
He went to the tournament hall.
He said something about
knowing a sure-fire way
to get front row seats
for all of us.
[LAUNCH gasps]
[BULMA giggles]
♪
[PATRON]
I can't see!
Buy some stilts.
That's sign language, people,
for "keep out or
I'll break your spine!"
Is that the ring?!
[giggles]
[OOLONG]
What are you doing?!
Don't you know a menacing
threat when you hear one?
I'm mean and red.
And I've got big horns!
[sobbing]
All right.
But you've got to
promise not to speak.
[PUAR]
Can I sit here?
What part of
"I'll break your spine"
don't you undersand? Uuh?!
I take that as a no.
Of course not.
[chuckles]
Eh, excuse my manners.
I'd love some company.
I've got the perfect seat
for you right over here.
Thanks, Oolong.
--[OOLONG] Puar?
--[PUAR] Ha-ha! He-he-he!
That was a dirty trick!
I see you two are
still up to your old ways.
Oh, Yamcha!
You were released?
Not exactly. But I wouldn't
miss this fight for the world.
Besides,
the food was terrible.
[BOTH]
Huh?
I belong here.
Oh, and hey, check it out!
We've got ya front row seats!
Mhm!
[CHUN] You're one of the most
gifted fighters I've ever faced.
Yet you undermine
your own potential
with your rotten ethics.
You bow to a false master.
Let me help you, Tien.
There is a better way.
I can unlock
your true potential,
but only if you let me inside...
inside... inside.. inside...
[TIEN grunts]
Relax. Just calm
down and relax.
Forget about that crazy old man.
He's just trying to confuse you.
Focus on your objective.
Tao must be avenged.
Goku must pay
for his transgression!
[TIEN] Hold onto
the memory of Tao.
Hold onto the memory of Tao!
Anger feeds strength,
and strength is power!
[SHEN] He's late.
What's he doing in there?
He'd better not be
shaving his head...
Punctuality before vanity,
I always say.
Strange. This is the
first time he's ever told me
to leave him alone.
It's probably a case of
nerves. Unusual for him.
But understandable
given his task.
Check on him. Maybe he
needs help with his tunic.
Yes, sir.
Tien? Are you--?
[gasps]
It's time.
Mm. Let's go.
[giggles]
Ready!
Well, you look great!
Thanks!
[chuckles]
[BOTH laugh]
Achoo!
[BULMA]
Mmm! Augh!
Ah! It's time. We have to go!
Okay, all together now.
Let's go!
And one, and two,
and one, and two,
and one, and two...
We're here to watch the
fight, not TV. Now let's go!
[CROWD cheering, whistling]
Somebody better get this
fight started soon or I will!
Take it easy, Launch. It'll
start soon enough. Calm down.
[SHEN grunts]
[ROSHI]
Mm?
[SHEN]
You should be ashamed.
Disguising yourself
as a contestant!
Do you need
recognition that badly?
[ROSHI] Not everyone
is as vain as you.
I just wanted to keep
an eye on my students.
[SHEN] You should keep
an eye on that waistline.
You looked pathetic up there!
[ROSHI] You're one
to talk, crane brain!
[SHEN]
Errr! You buffoon!
[ROSHI] By the way,
nice ninja pajamas.
[SHEN]
You wouldn't know fashion
if it slapped you in the face!
[ROSHI grumbles]
[YAMCHA]
Master Roshi?
[ROSHI]
Heh?
Who were you talking to?
Oh, you heard that?
We'd love to hear more
about your waistline issue.
I do not have
a waistline issue!
Heh!
[ROSHI]
Mmm...
Yeah!
[distant cheering, chattering]
Uuh!
Hey, Goku!
[KRILLIN] Good luck, Goku.
I know you can do it.
[drum rolls]
[gong rings]
The final match in the
World Martial Arts Tournament
is about to begin!
[CROWD cheering, hollering]
We began with 182 fighters
gathered from
around the world.
Eight of which advanced
to the semi-finals.
Now there are but
two fighters remaining,
one of which will become the
new Master of Martial Arts,
not to mention walk away
with a cool 500,000 zeni!
Not bad for a few days' work,
wouldn't you say?
Ha-ha-ha! Who will it be?
While you ponder that,
let me provide
a little background
on our contestants.
First up... Tien Shinhan.
[CROWD cheering]
This skilled performer
has become
the fighter to watch
during the tournament.
Prized pupil of the
Crane Hermit, Master Shen,
it is widely regarded that Tien
Shinhan's abilities rival,
if not surpass
those of his master.
We've already witnessed
an incredible display
of his strength as he left
Yamcha with a broken leg,
and forced previous
champion, Jackie Chun,
out of the semi-finals.
Combine that with the fact
that his average
fight time is 32.5 seconds,
and you have a glimpse
into the awesome power
that is Tien Shinhan!
Our second contestant is Goku!
[KRILLIN]
Goku!
No matter what happens,
you have to beat Tien.
Right!
[CROWD cheering]
This pint-sized warrior serves
the Turtle Hermit, Master Roshi,
who coincidentally
just happens to be
the archrival of Master Shen.
Aside from the fact that
he received second place
in the last tournament,
Goku's list of victories
would leave even
the most veteran fighter
green with envy.
He most recently dazzled
the audience with his
one-punch dismissal of world-
renowned champion Pamput
and the unique
disappearing act he used
to unceremoniously remove
Krillin from the ring
in the previous match.
His average fight time
is 35.7 seconds.
[ROSHI] This should be
one heck of a finale.
We're with you, Goku!
Heh-heh!
Stop with the yackin' and
start with the smackin'!
[CROWD screaming]
Typical.
How embarrassing! Roshi?
[ROSHI] I've got to
find a better seat!
Hello.
You're not allowed
to be back here, Master.
This area is reserved
for participants only.
[ROSHI] It's all right.
I'm sure they won't mind.
Now the battle to see
who will become the Champion
of the 22nd World Martial
Arts Tournament begins.
Get ready!
Watch closely. You may never
see a fight like this again.
Right!
Why is everyone silent?
Be quiet!
[SHEN]
My brother was no saint.
But he deserved better than to
die at the hands of a child.
Roshi's child!
[SHEN] Retribution
won't bring Tao back,
but it will certainly
brighten my day.
Begin!
Uh!
Oh no!
[TIEN laughs]
[TIEN]
Dodon!
[GOKU]
Uuugh!
[ALL gasp]
[grunts]
That was short and sweet,
but effective.
Look, Master, it's Goku!
[GOKU]
He-haaa!
[CROWD gasps, cheers]
He shouldn't
scare us like that.
It'll take more than
a little fall to stop him. Hm!
[GOKU grunts]
Ah! He's vanished again!
Truly one of Goku's
greatest techniques!
[rapid boinging]
[boinging increases]
Heh! Tag! Haaa!
No!
[GOKU groans]
Now you'll learn what it means
to suffer the wrath
of Tien Shinhan!
--[TIEN yells]
--[GOKU groans]
[bellows]
[ALL gasp, murmur]
[chuckles intensely]
Hang in there!
I've never seen
punches like that.
It's like a machine gun.
[TIEN grunts, yells]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[BULMA whimpers]
[BOTH whimper]
[LAUNCH]
Uh...
[BOTH]
Uuh...!
[SHEN chuckles]
[groans]
[TIEN] The only thing
more gratifying
than watching you suffer
is knowing that somewhere,
Tao is smiling right now.
[NARRATOR]
Has Goku met his defeat?
Will Tien claim his vengeance
and the championship?
The action continues
next time on Dragon Ball!