[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball...
Never tangle with
the Red Ribbon Army.
All available men!
Get down there and
find that Dragon Ball!
[NARRATOR] Colonel Silver
and the Red Ribbon Army
ambushed the Ox King's village
in search of a Dragon Ball.
The oversized
Ox King struggled
against the army's
awesome firepower...
but ultimately, his brute
strength was no match
for Colonel Silver's
advanced weaponry.
Ahh! I can't see!
At last... it's all mine.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Emperor Pilaf
saw his opportunity
to grab the prize.
[SILVER] Get him!
[NARRATOR] Colonel Silver
watched the Dragon Ball
slip away as
Emperor Pilaf reached
the safety of
his flying fortress.
The little blue tyrant's
sneakiness paid off this time...
but for how long?
You won't escape me!
Hey! What's that?
[CHICHI] It's gigantic!
You're safe now.
Whew, I sure hope so!
Help! Help!
Goku! Help me!!
L-L-L-Leggo... of my...
...TAIL!
[GOKU] Nimbus!
[PILAF]
He, he, he, he... Yeess...
there's nothing like the glow
from a genuine
Dragon Ball is there...?
Not that you two would know,
but it's un-mis-takable!
Unmistakable?
Then how come he paid all
that money for that fake ball...
Hey, what did you say?
Ow! Nothing.
So about those army people...
Are they still chasing us?
Yes, they're following,
but for the time being
they're keeping their distance.
I think we're still safely
outside of their attack range.
I wonder who, they are...
[SOLDIER A] Who are they,
Colonel Silver?
Probably some reckless
millionaires looking for kicks.
They don't know what
they're getting into...
Now less questions,
and more flying!
[SOLDIER A] Yes sir!
[SILVER] All soldiers, man
your fighter jets immediately.
Stand by for my coordinates.
What was that for?
I'll ask the questions!
This is my garden!
Who are you people?
I don't like her tone of voice!
[CHICHI squeals]
Huh?
[SOLDIER] Augh!
[CHICHI] Stay away!
Aaah!
I want my daddy!
Someone help me!
You're not
supposed to hit girls!
[sobs]
Where did'ya
take the Ox King?
He's that way.
You're okay!
[CHICHI] Oh, Daddy!
Let's get out of here!
Well look at that!
[CHICHI] Are you okay, Dad?
[GOKU] Sir, you gotta be strong!
[CHICHI] We need you!
[SOLDIER A] It's getting foggy.
Visibility is poor.
[SOLDIER A] It-it's impossible!
Huh? What?
[SOLDIER A] They've
vanished into thin air!
Up! Go above the clouds!
[SILVER] Hmm... Not here...
Well, I guess the hunt is on...
Serves 'em right!
Oh yea, who's got it now?
Hey, who were those guys?
Did you know them?
Ah, well, no, but given my past,
I must have some
enemies out there.
You see, I used
to be a very bad man.
But that's beside the point.
They crashed your party!
Uh? Party?
What are you talking about?
I wasn't having a party?
You're terrible!
How can you even
pretend you don't know?
[GOKU] I-I don't know what?
Well, isn't this interesting?
You sure seemed to
enjoy the wedding feast
we prepared for you.
Feast?
What, do you mean
those apples I ate?
No... the... you were...
Look, there!
[SOLDIER A]
Hey! We're down here!
We're down here! Hey! Look down!
Heeey! Heeey...! Down here!
Headquarters.
This is Silver.
We have come under fire,
and have lost our
fix on the target...
Can you pinpoint their location
with the Dragon Radar?
So, if that wasn't Goku
at dinner, where was he?
Oh-h!
He was with me.
He came right out
of an apple tree
when I was at the pond...
We were talking about
how nice it will be
to be married and have a family!
Then, who fooled me
at the table tonight?
Well whoever they were,
I'll bet they were
after the Dragon Ball.
The Dragon Ball?
You mean like the one
you got from my castle?
[GOKU] Yes... there
are seven balls in all.
One of them
belonged to my grandpa.
That's the one I'm looking for.
Gohan's? It was
really Gohan's?
Uh huh...
[GOKU] Let's see
what the radar says.
Oh, it's moved so far away!
Thanks, I gotta go! Bye!
[CHICHI] Goku!
Huh?
What about the wedding?
I'll be back!
I'll try some of that
next time! Goodbye!
Goku!
[CHICHI] Uh!
[GOKU] See ya later, Chichi!
[CHICHI] Goku!
"Wedding" is not a food!
Be patient.
That boy is on a quest...
But he'll be back. One day.
[STAFF OFFICER] The radar shows
the ball is now stationary.
[SILVER] Sir we've just
reached the coordinates.
Need to verify the position.
I have PX 303
southwest, correct?
[STAFF OFFICER] Roger.
It's within a 1 mile radius
of your current location.
[SILVER] There's nothing
here but a barren desert.
They wouldn't have
ditched the ball here
after such a hard
time getting it.
It doesn't make sense!
[STAFF OFFICER]
The radar is highly accurate.
Your current
position is correct!
Now you're wasting time.
You can mull over
how much 'sense'
all of this makes to you
while you're
conducting your search.
You had better get started.
It'll be dark soon.
[GOKU] Hey, did
I turn the wrong way?
I thought I was
reading it right...
[SILVER thinking]
If that huge fortress landed
or crashed I would
surely see it out here.
I don't think we'll
find anything around here.
That radar's broken! Ya' know?
I agree, I think
they spent too much
on that piece of junk!
Oh-h yeah, big money.
Huh? Huh? Uh?
Hey, come 'ere!
You find it?
No, no...
Aaaah!
[PILAF] Welcome
to my humble abode.
Who's that?
I am Emperor Pilaf.
[PILAF] I presume you
belong to some army,
what with those snappy
uniforms of yours.
Why don't you come work for me?
Never! Just let us go!
[PILAF] Well, you may change
your mind soon enough!
Look at this!
What is it?
[PILAF] Put it on my monitor.
[PILAF] That kid!
He's after me again!
[PILAF] What does it take
to get rid of this pest?
Well, according to this,
it's supposed to be right here!
[SILVER] This is Silver.
Come in, Search Party.
Answer me!
Is there anybody down there?
This is Colonel Silver!
Do you read?
Search Party, come in!
[GOKU] Huh?
[PILAF] He's coming this way!
[SHU] Do you think
he noticed the camera?
[GOKU sighs and urinates]
Ew! No, No, No!
What the...
Who in the heck is that kid?
The planes!
An underground base!
Silver to base...
Silver to base.
I found the enemy's
headquarters.
It is at PX 303 SW.
Send reinforcements now!
[STAFF OFFICER]
Roger, we'll send Brown's army.
Just sit tight and wait.
[SILVER] There's no
time to wait, you imbecile!
Welcome, young friend.
You're not my friend!
No, of course not.
Give me my
grandpa's Dragon Ball!
Nyaaaah!
Sorry, I had a different
present in mind.
I know you!
You're the monster that stole
our Dragon Balls last time!
[PILAF] What's this?
[GOKU] Kamehame...
Haa!
My robot...
[MAI] They're attacking
from the air!
[SILVER] All right, I've got
you just where I want you now!
Don't just stand
there, you fools!
Man the guns!
Sire!
Are we gonna retreat?
[PILAF] What a stupid question.
Of course we are!
[GOKU] Wait!
[GOKU] Get back here!
[PILAF] Shu, hit the switch!
No sweat!
You won't get away from me!
Well, well, well,
here it comes.
Hit the gas! Full throttle!
NOW! Let's go!
Hey! Nimbus! Nimbus!
[coughing]
Ahh, they'll
never take you away...
My precious...
Emperor!
We're hidden by the smoke!
They won't be able to see us!
Thank goodness!
We're saved!
Of course we are!
Nyahahahahahaha!
Ohh!
[SILVER snickers]
[NARRATOR] Emperor Pilaf has
been cornered by the fierce
Red Ribbon Army and stripped
of his prized possession.
But where is Goku?
Did he escape the
explosion in one piece?
You'll have to watch to find
out--next time on Dragon Ball!