[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
in his quest to bring
his friends back to life,
Goku used his Power Pole to
launch high into the sky,
and connected with a mystical
sanctuary known as the Lookout.
[GOKU]
I made it!
[NARRATOR]
Climbing onboard,
Goku had his first
encounter with someone
he'll get to know very well.
[POPO]
Nice to meet you!
If you want to see
the Earth's Guardian,
you'll have to fight
with Mr. Popo first.
Let's have a match!
[GOKU laughs]
[grunts]
Ouch!
[NARRATOR] Not only did Piccolo
take the lives of
Chiaotzu, Krillin,
Master Roshi, and others,
he also destroyed
the Eternal Dragon
so that no one could
use the Dragon Balls
to wish them back to life.
The mysterious Guardian is
Goku's last hope to save them,
but he clearly has a
new problem on his hands.
[POPO] You have quite an
impressive power, little Goku,
but you have no idea
how to use it correctly.
You cannot beat me.
Please, go home.
[whines]
[NARRATOR]
Goku's journey to the clouds
might have been made in vain.
Unless he proves himself
in this fight,
he cannot visit the Guardian,
and Mr. Popo seems to
have his number down.
Can Goku find another way?
Find out today, on Dragon Ball!
Looking after the
Guardian of the Earth
keeps me pleasantly
busy, little Goku.
While I do enjoy your company,
it is time for you to leave.
Wait! I can't leave!
Korin said coming up here
was the only way
to bring back
everybody Piccolo hurt!
They were my best friends!
I'm not going!
[growls]
[POPO]
You have a temper, don't you?
[GOKU]
Yaah!
[yells]
[grunting, growling]
[grunts]
[POPO] I already told you,
you can't win.
Come on!
[grunts]
So persistent,
however, lacking in mental
and physical discipline.
You'll be a great fighter...
[GOKU whines]
[POPO]
...but not yet.
I can't believe it!
That hurt even more
than Piccolo's punches!
Yes, you beat him and so assumed
you were the
toughest in the world.
But learn this now:
No matter how strong you are,
there will always be someone
stronger who comes along.
To stay on top,
you must keep pushing past
what you think is strength.
[GOKU]
Mm-hmm...
I feel pretty weak, now.
I'm glad we had this little
chat. Now go on home, please.
What?! No! I have to
see the Guardian,
so my friends aren't dead any
longer than they have to be!
You wouldn't like it
if you were dead
and your friends just
gave up on you, right?
Well, I won't do it!
I'm sure they have
great board games to play.
Besides, you're not
strong enough to beat me.
Aah! Then I can
stay here and train!
[POPO]
Train? For what?
[laughs]
You know! Until I'm
strong enough to beat you!
Ah, yes. Well, I guess so,
but don't leave
skid marks on the tiles.
Thanks a lot, Mr. Popo!
See ya soon!
[GOKU chuckles]
What a good-hearted boy he is.
I bet Mr. Popo is the
strongest in the universe!
I hope Goku's doing okay,
wherever he is.
He said he was gonna go see some
sort of "Guardian of the Earth."
Yeah, poor kid really
thinks he can do something
to bring Krillin and
Master Roshi back.
If anybody can do it, I guess
a mystical planet-protector
would be the one.
[PUAR] You really think the
Guardian exists, Yamcha?
What would it look like?
[YAMCHA]
I don't know.
Tall, great hair, really
big muscles, I guess.
Who even cares?
It's not like we'll ever see it.
Oh, can it pig!
We've already seen
the world's most evil person.
Maybe we'll see
the purest one, too.
Yeah. There's no telling
what to expect at this point.
All I know is if there's
a Guardian, Goku will find it.
That's right.
[chuckles]
Well, if it does exist,
two things are certain.
It's got the face of a pig,
and it sure ain't a lady!
[growls]
[OOLONG groans]
Why don't I take you
to a men's club?!
I'm sure they like pork chops!
My mistake.
[growls]
[TIEN] Goku. Our last fight
against Piccolo
showed I was nothing
compared to you.
But if a kid
can reach such powers,
think what a
trained master can do.
At the next World Martial Arts
Tournament I will surpass you!
[GOKU chuckles]
We'll see about that.
[growls]
[TIEN thinking] I'll work
hard to beat you, Goku.
So make sure you get home safe!
[yelling, grunting]
I'm tired!
The Lookout is at a
very high altitude, Goku.
The air's quite thin,
so breathing is
much more difficult.
To train without passing out,
you need to get rid of
your redundant moves.
Energy's far too precious
up here to be wasted.
How do I not waste it?
You must be more
tranquil than the sky,
yet quicker than lightning.
But the sky doesn't move.
And when I see lightning,
it's really quick!
[laughs]
Sounds pretty tricky to me!
Watch me. Empty your
mind of thoughts.
Do you notice how quiet it
is up here when nobody talks?
It's kinda creepy.
Oh! Sorry, I forgot.
Goku, you're just making
your eyes go blurry.
That's not the same thing
as emptying your mind.
Wha--? Wow, this really is hard!
When that's done, you can
focus on not being a slug.
Waugh!
Hey! How'd you do that?!
I didn't see you move one bit!
There aren't two
Mr. Popos here, are there?
I can see you're puzzled. You're
scratching your right cheek.
That's even weirder!
You have eyes on
the back of your head, too?
[POPO]
Nope.
Then how come you can
see what I'm doing?
The answer is the same reason
why you couldn't see me moving.
You're only using
your eyes to see.
True sight requires all
your senses, my young friend.
Feel the movements of the air
around me,
and then you'll be
able to see me.
[GOKU gasps]
So I've gotta see
without my eyes
and be like sky and lightning?
That's a lot of stuff.
No wonder you keep beating me.
Well, the Guardian of Earth
has taught me many things
in our years together.
I'd like to think
that I make him proud.
Whoa! Are you saying the
Guardian's even stronger
than you are?!
Oh yes, much stronger.
I'm a mouse compared to him.
[POPO]
Are you discouraged?
Not at all!
Now I'm more excited!
Two guys stronger than me,
who can beat me up
without even trying?
[GOKU laughs]
Yeah!
Goku. You're a peculiar boy.
Wait a second. If this Guardian
is stronger than both of us,
why didn't he come down
and beat Piccolo?
I am afraid his role
is not that simple.
Hey, I've got it!
I'm gonna stay here forever!
[GOKU chuckles, laughs]
[GOKu] Or at least until
I get strong enough
to beat both you guys!
Then I'm sure you'll help!
[GOKU]
So, where d'you wanna start?
[DISPTCH] Come in,
Patrol Fifteen, come in.
We've got reports of
an unidentified intruder
in the northeast
corner of the park.
Investigate immediately.
[BOTH gasp]
[OFFICER A]
What is that?
You think it was shot?
I don't see any kind
of an entrance wound.
Nah, we were just a
hundred yards away.
We would've heard a gun.
This is something else.
Whatcha got?
Heavy feet.
Looks human to me.
Poacher, maybe.
Should we call backup?
Nah.
Stop!
Look, it's just a kid.
Hey! Wait up!
Whatcha doin' here,
little sport? Did you get lost?
What's your name? Who're your
parents? Are they here, too?
You shouldn't be walking
around out here by yourself.
You're safe now
that we've found you,
but there's a
poacher in the area.
Whoa, now, kid. Take it easy!
This isn't a cap gun, you know!
[yells]
Come any closer and I'll shoot!
I mean it! I mean it!
You freak! You're the one who
killed that bear, aren't you?
I... I-I said stay back!
[yelping]
Get back to the bikes!
My parents? Just one, Piccolo,
and he was kind enough to
give me everything he had.
I move less than
the sky, and yet...
...I move quicker
than lightning!
Always so cheerful
and determined.
Tell you what. I'll assist you.
Yay! I was hoping
you'd teach me how!
My brain hurts
when I think too much!
No, no, Goku. You still
have to learn on your own.
I'll just give hints.
That's stingy!
You're carrying a bell, correct?
Bell? Oh, hey!
Korin just gave me one.
[GOKU]
He said I'd need it.
So now what?
Try one more time
to hit Mr. Popo.
Okay, but I've learned
a whole lot. Be warned!
Here goes.
Ow!
Darn it, I'm still not
quick enough!
And what else?
You back-flipped?
What happened before
you attacked me?
Well, let's see.
I gave you my bell.
[gasps]
You moved like an acrobat
to dodge my attack,
and the bell
never even made a peep!
How'd you do that?
Maybe you should try it.
Must've slipped. Hold on.
That's weird.
The bell's quiet around you,
but every time I move
it likes to ring.
I know! It's a trick, right?
Go home, Goku.
[GOKU]
No, wait! Don't leave, uh...
Did I say something wrong?
I look after the Earth's
Guardian, my boy.
I don't have time
for shenanigans.
Sorry. It just reminded me of
a prank Master Roshi pulled.
At least, Krillin told me it
was prank when we were finished,
but maybe it was for real.
Give it a whirl.
Krillin said Master Roshi
had pasted the jar to his head.
But maybe there is a way to move
that keeps water
from getting splashy,
and bells from ringing!
Water from getting splashy...
Hey! Water spills when you move
it one way
and then back in
the other direction.
That's like a bell!
If you just move it once,
it doesn't work.
You have to keep
jingling it back and forth!
And those are
the redundant moves.
Then I win!
See, you're smart
when you try, Goku.
But knowing it won't be enough.
Right, I get it. I have to learn
how to really move that way.
But once I keep the bell quiet,
I can beat you, can't I?
Perhaps, but it could take
years of intense training.
And after you've
learned the technique,
there's still the chance you
won't be able to get past me.
[chuckles sheepishly]
You must decide.
Will you commit to years of
training that could end in vain?
You bet! I'll do whatever it
takes to bring my friends back!
[VOICE]
That's good to hear.
[GOKU] Hey, who's there?
Is that you, Mr. Guardian?
[POPO]
Exactly.
[GOKU]
And he's talking to me?
[GUARDIAN]
I will meet with you now.
[GOKU gasps]
You mean it? Before the years
of training? Ha ha ha! Yeah!
You're a fortunate boy,
Goku. This is rare.
[GOKU]
Thanks, Mr. Guardian!
[GOKU laughs]
[YAJIROBE] What's the deal?
Goku's been gone a while!
If all's going smoothly,
he should be seeing
the big boss about right now.
Why's everyone making
such a big deal about it?
Didn't you say Goku's already
seen this Guardian guy before?
I was using some poetic license.
Trust me, this meeting
should be more fun
than you at a breakfast bar.
[KORIN chuckles]
[POPO]
Don't move closer than this.
[GOKU] Okay! This is exciting,
isn't it? Wow, I can't wait!
[GOKU laughs]
Where is he?
Remember, stay put.
[GOKU]
Oh boy!
[laughs]
Ah... Aahh!
Piccolo!
I should've known
that you were still alive,
you big monster!
Goku, wait. No!
[GOKU growls]
Give me back my friends!
[GOKU groans]
Let go of me! [growls]
You don't understand! He's the
bad guy I told you about!
It is you who fails to
understand. This is not Piccolo.
I should've known Korin
wouldn't explain it to you.
[GOKU]
Whoa!
Did you say Korin?
He thinks he's very funny.
[GUARDIAN]
There's a good reason
you mistook me
for Piccolo, my boy.
Ages ago,
we two beings were one.
A single coin
with two opposing sides.
My name is Kami, and I am indeed
the guardian of this planet.
But it wasn't always that way.
What do you mean?
Guardians are a mortal lot,
much like you.
There was a guardian before me,
and I sensed that his end
was approaching.
I made the same trek that
you did, up to this Lookout,
hoping to become his successor.
But he turned his back on me.
[KAMI] I strongly believed that
I was destined to replace him,
but in his great wisdom,
he saw in me a side
I was too proud to admit.
You see, a guardian's
motives must be pure.
Yet in me was a selfish desire
for its power and control,
a side that thrived
on bitterness and hate.
For many brutal years
I meditated and trained,
until I was finally able
to separate my impure desire
and drive it out of my body.
That evil became Piccolo.
While in my purified form,
I remained at the Lookout
and became the next Guardian,
Piccolo went down to the
Earth to incite disorder.
It's been a great
source of guilt for me.
But you, Goku, have stopped
him in his boldest assault.
And in gratitude, I will
give ear to your request.
[laughs]
But on one condition. You must
remain here and train under me
for as long as
my own motives require.
Of course!
I wanted to do that anyway!
Now I can tell you which
friends to bring back, right?
I know. Krillin, Chiaotzu,
Master Roshi, Nam,
all the other fighters.
Unfortunately,
my powers as guardian
will not bring them back.
Uh...
The one being that has that
ability is Shenron, the Dragon.
I guess I'll simply
have to recreate him,
and let the Earthlings use
the Dragon Balls again.
You can really do that, Kami?
[KAMI]
Yes, but I do so begrudgingly.
From now on, Goku,
you must take greater care
to protect your friends
and secure the power
of the dragon.
I promise to!
Good. I will hold you to that.
Now, Mr. Popo,
I would like to begin recreating
the Eternal Dragon immediately.
--[POPO] Yes, Kami.
--Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you, thank
you, Mr. Kami-Guardian!
[GOKU laughs]
[POPO laughs]
Yeah!
[NARRATOR]
Goku has won his wish.
His friends and the Eternal
Dragon will soon be revived.
But what will
Goku's training entail?