[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball,
the tournament
semi-finals began
as Jackie Chun
battled Tien Shinhan.
Confident the
mirror-image technique
would stop his adversary,
Jackie overlooked
Tien's incredible sight
and paid the price.
Fortunately,
Jackie Chun decided to take
a more hands-on approach.
What followed was
the most ferocious fight
the tournament
had seen in years.
[TIEN grunts]
[NARRATOR] Which took
its toll on the combatants.
[TIEN] It makes no sense
that an old man should be
so agile and skillful.
Whoever he is,
he's more powerful
than anyone I've ever faced.
[CHUN]
He's just a kid,
but he's taken everything
I've thrown at him,
and keeps coming back for more!
[distant cheering, hollering]
[YAMCHA]
Nothing but noise!
Man, I'd give anything
to be able to see the fight.
If only my leg would cooperate!
[knock, knock]
Hm? Yes?
[door clicks open]
[door clicks shut]
[distant cheering, hollering]
It's not exactly
the front row,
but it beats the window.
That's very kind of you, ma'am.
[radio static]
[ANNOUNCER ON RADIO]
...trading punch for punch!
The only word to describe
this fight is severe!
Jackie Chun and
Tien Shinhan are embroiled
in what could be...
[YAMCHA] Even Jackie Chun is
having trouble beating Tien.
Is this guy human?!
Just don't get too excited
and jump out of the bed!
[ANNOUNCER] Who will win this
battle is anyone's guess!
[CROWD cheering]
Problem is,
they're both good.
Yep.
[SHEN chuckles]
[TIEN yells]
[ANNOUNCER]
Huh?
[OOLONG] I can't see!
The suns in my eyes!
[PUAR]
Here, does this help?
[OOLONG]
Uh... I would say no.
[TIEN yells, groans]
[TIEN yells]
Come on, hang in there!
--Go Jackie! Get him!
--Jackie! You can do it!
[LAUNCH sneezes]
[ALL]
Uh-uhh!
[LAUNCH] Come on! Stop dancing
around and fight like real men!
This is boring! Move it!
Not now, Launch.
[TIEN bellows]
[CHUN groans]
[BOTH]
Aah!
Don't fall!
[SHEN]
Tien's got him now!
[CHUN]
Hmm?
[CROWD murmurs]
What?
[CROWD cheering, whistling]
[hollers]
You're finished!
[yells, groans]
[grunts]
Someone should
teach you some manners.
Now... Lesson one...
[TIEN groans]
[CHUN]
Never upset your elders!
Jackie Chun is one step
from falling out of the ring!
Tien Shinhan needs only to
move him a few inches further!
Don't fall, Jackie. Hold on.
[SHEN]
Tien is taking too long!
[LAUNCH grunts]
Can't breathe!
[gasping]
Failing to push
Jackie Chun from the ring,
Tien Shinhan has
resorted to head-butting.
[TIEN yells]
Your reign is over! Uaaah!
[CROWD cheering, whistling]
[PUAR, OOLONG gasp]
[LAUNCH]
Whoa!
[BOTH gasps]
[grunts]
You are one of the most gifted
fighters I've ever faced.
Yet you undermine
your own potential
with your rotten ethics.
You're not my master, gramps!
I don't care what you
or anyone else thinks.
I'm here to win this match!
Take the chip off your
shoulder and get serious.
Be careful what
you ask for, old man.
You don't want
to see me serious.
What?! Are you saying
that so far
you've just been
clowning around?!
[TIEN chuckles]
He's lying!
If he had more strength,
he would've
used it before now!
[grunts]
[BOTH]
Ha! Hm-hmmm...
[TIEN grunts]
Huh? What's he doing?
How's this for clowning?
Solar Flare!
[BOTH yell]
[ALL yell]
[TIEN bellows]
[CROWD screaming]
I... can't see!
[TIEN bellows]
What--What happened?!
I couldn't see!
You're lucky.
You should be dead,
but I can't join another
match if I kill someone.
Still, as far as this fight
is concerned, you're finished!
[CROWD murmurs, groans]
[BULMA sobbing]
[TIEN laughs]
Before we go on,
I'd like to say
that even though
there's no rule against
using such a technique,
it was a dirty trick!
[SHEN chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER] We have seen
no movement from Jackie Chun
since the terrible
burst of light.
However, tournament
guidelines call for
a countdown nonetheless.
One... two... three...
--[KRILLIN] My eyes hurt.
--[ANNOUNCER] ...four...
--[GOKU] Wake up, Jackie!
--[ANNOUNCER] ...five...
And six... seven...
[TIEN chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER]
...eight... nine...
Uh!
Te--huh?!
[CHUN groans]
What a light! We're lucky
we can still see.
Yeah, real lucky.
Impossible!
Thanks for the tan.
But if you're going
to try that again,
at least pass out sunglasses.
He's up! Jackie Chun
is back on his feet again!
It's nothing
short of miraculous,
but the fight is still on!
[OOLONG groans] Is anyone
else seeing spots?
I always see spots.
Chun may be standing,
but it doesn't look like
he's fully recovered.
Yamcha's counting
on you, Jackie!
Ignore the pain
and keep fighting!
I wonder!
[CHUN'S neck cracking]
Old man! How did
you recover so fast?
Look... Such knowledge
is beyond your reach
until you leave
your evil ways behind.
You've allowed yourself
to be led down
a short and destructive path.
You bow to a false master.
That's enough!
Listen to my words, Tien.
The truth is always upsetting
when you choose to live a lie.
No! You're just
trying to confuse me!
I won't listen to
the ravings of a lunatic!
[SHEN]
Mmm...
What are you hiding... Jackie?
[TIEN yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[TIEN chuckles]
Careful, my boy. You run
the risk of getting sloppy.
That last charge was weak,
even for you.
It was enough to catch
you off guard, old man!
But not to defeat me. And that
is your objective, isn't it?
You are not focussed on
the present, the here and now.
Your mind is
scattered like dust.
I don't understand why Jackie
is still talking to him.
Do you think maybe he's too
tired to continue fighting?
No! Are you crazy?!
Jackie Chun doesn't
get tired. He's invincible!
This is all part of his plan!
[GOKU]
You think so?
[KRILLIN]
I know so!
Oh... I guess that
makes sense... sort of.
All of your values have
been tainted and jaded.
[TIEN grunts]
It's not your fault, really.
The Crane Hermit has always
excelled at deception.
Uh! He's preaching!
Ah...
Hm.
[SHEN] Hear my thoughts,
Jackie Chun.
You are surrounded
by fans that adore you.
Especially the pretty
ladies in front.
Listen to them. Turn around.
They're speaking to you.
[CHUN]
Heh?!
What are they saying?!
Gotcha! I knew it was you
all along, you faker!
Uh?!
[SHEN] Tien Shinhan! Don't be
fooled by that troublemaker.
He's really
Master Roshi in disguise!
[gasps]
[CHUN]
Hm?
Did you really think that
bad wig would fool anyone?
You--You know who I am?
All right, yes.
I'm Master Roshi.
[TIEN]
Uh.
But my identity doesn't make
my words any less true.
Don't throw away your ability
by giving in to Shen!
You're young. There's still
time to change your course!
Enough! Your lectures
are meaningless to me!
Wa--I can't hear them.
I wonder what they're saying.
It's probably
just a distraction.
It makes no difference
to me who you are. Hm!
But now that I know,
I've got the perfect weapon.
Tien, you're making
a big mistake.
No, gramps!
I'm correcting one!
Uuh!
[TIEN grunting]
Uh, what's he doing now?
This could be very bad!
--[LAUNCH grunts]
--[TURTLE] Aah!
Ka... me...
Kamehame-ha!
[TIEN]
...ha... me...
He--He wouldn't!
Ha!
No! You're aiming
for the audience!
[GROUP screams]
[CROWD screams]
[ALL screaming]
[CHUN grunting]
[BULMA, PUAR, OOLONG whimper]
Is it over?
I sure hope so.
[CHUN grunts]
In a strange role-reversal,
Crane alumni Tien Shinhan
used a signature move
of the Turtle School,
the Kamehame-ha Wave!
Wow!
Did you see Jackie?! The
wave bounced right off him!
[TIEN chuckles]
As you just witnessed,
there is no technique
which I cannot master.
You're fighting a losing battle.
Anything you use on me,
I can throw right back!
You could do with some humility.
I could teach you that, too.
[TIEN grunts]
Hm. It all comes
so easy to you.
But you must keep a level head
if you want to succeed.
I can show you how.
You sound like a broken record!
[CHUN sighs]
That's encouraging. Now let's
hope some of it sinks in.
He looks a little... upset.
What's he doing?
What's this? Jackie Chun
has turned his back
on his competitor!
Is this some new technique?
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
As my season ends,
so a new one begins.
[CROWD gasps]
Aah!
[yells]
No, Jackie!
This can't be!
There must be
a reason but... what?
[ANNOUNCER]
Whether by accident or design,
Jackie Chun is out of the ring.
Tien Shinhan is the winner!
Impossible!
[sighs]
[CROWD whispers]
[LAUNCH]
Silence!
You're disturbing
my concentration.
But why?
[CHUN humming]
Why aren't you fighting?!
[SHEN] Roshi quit because he
knew you would have beaten him.
He couldn't
bear the humiliation.
You are his superior
in every way!
No... He was not afraid,
and, if anything,
he was holding back.
Jackie...
How come?
Ah! It looks like
the two of you are up next.
Uh! He's right,
I almost forgot!
We're going to be fighting
each other in the next match!
Oh yeah!
[chuckles]
It's all in your
hands now, boys. Good luck.
[NARRATOR]
Tien Shinhan has advanced
to the Championship Round.
Who will be his opponent?
Krillin... or Goku?
Friends become rivals
as they battle to see
who will take the last spot
in the Championship Round.
Don't miss match six of
this exciting tournament,
next time on Dragon Ball!