[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Goku was honored as the champion
of the 23rd World
Martial Arts Tournament
after defeating
his archrival, Junior.
[NARRATOR] After saying
goodbye to Master Roshi
and his other friends,
Goku embarked on his
Nimbus cloud toward
his next great adventure, life
with his new fiancée, ChiChi.
[GOKU] I don't see your
dad's castle, ChiChi.
It is right around
here isn't it?
Don't ask me. You didn't
want directions, remember?
What is it with men? Why are
you allergic to assistance?
I'm not.
I was being sarcastic.
Oh, your father's gonna
be in for a surprise
when he finds out
we're getting married.
I just hope he thinks
it's a good one.
Uh. We'll know soon enough!
Huh?
[NARRATOR] Asking a father for
his daughter's hand in marriage
is a daunting task. But Goku's
anxiety is understandable,
for ChiChi's father not
only governs his household,
but an entire kingdom as well.
He is the Ox King,
a mighty ruler,
whose serene land is made even
more so on this beautiful day.
But, all of that
is about to change.
[munching]
[munching continues]
Uh?
--[GOKU burps]
--[CHICHI groans]
[munching]
[slurping]
[OX KING] It's good to have
ya home again, ChiChi.
As the Ox King, I'm
fearless, but as a father,
I'm entitled to worry.
[munching]
Hm? Uh?
[OX KING] I expected you to
return with news of the fights,
not a husband.
--[GOKU sighs]
--[OX KING chuckles]
As far as surprises go,
this is a good one, I think.
You've grown into
a fine young man.
You share your
grandfather's strong spirit,
and his fierce appetite.
[OX KING laughs]
--[CHICHI, OX KING laugh]
--[GOKU] Huh? Uh? Uh.
[OX KING]
Your kids have done your part.
So, I guess, being
father of the bride,
it's time for me to do mine.
[GOKU grunts]
Eh?
[OX KING gulps]
Ahh! I'm going to give my
baby girl the biggest wedding
this world has ever seen!
Oh, we can handle the
arrangements ourselves.
Right, Goku?
Hmm? Oh, sure. No problem.
Nonsense! There's something...
I've been saving for you.
What?
[clattering, banging]
[CHICHI]
Papa?
[OX KING]
Oh...
--Huh?
--[OX KING] Here it is.
Ah...
[OX KING]
I hope you like it.
[CHICHI]
What is it?
[squeals]
Uh?
Perfect!
[OX KING]
It belonged to your mother
and her mother before that.
[sighs] Mama.
It was her wish that
you should have it.
Oh, my.
[CHICHI sighs. giggles]
[OX KING] Your mother looked
so beautiful in that dress.
And so will you, my dear.
[CHICHI sighs, giggles]
Papa, this means more to
me than you'll ever know.
In a way, it's like
mom will be there.
It's gorgeous. Isn't it, Goku?
What?
Oh, sure. Right.
Whatever you decide to wear.
I-I know it'll look great.
Hm, yes.
[OX KING]
That's not true.
Huh?
It would be unthinkable for you
to wear anything but that dress.
It has been in our
family for generations.
Mh-hm.
[sighs, giggles]
[CROWD chatters]
A wedding is more
than a celebration.
It is a precious
milestone in one's life.
Hm? I appreciate
everyone's help.
Thanks.
Hm?
[MAN panting]
--[CHICHI laughs]
--[GOKU grunts]
[INSTRUCTOR]
One, two, three! Tempo! Tempo!
My speech is ready!
The mood is set!
All we need to make things
perfect is good weather!
Hmm.
[rumbling]
Uh?
Huh? Uh...
[MAN yelping]
--[STAFF yelping]
--[OX KING grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
What's wrong?
Earthquake!
[ALL yelp]
[ALL scream]
Take cover!
--[CROWD screams]
--Everyone, get out!
[ALL scream]
[GOKU grunts]
--[CHICHI] Uh. Wait!
--[GOKU] Ah? Uh.
What about the wedding dress?
It's in my father's room!
[OX KING]
I'll get the dress!
Goku, take ChiChi and
get her to safety! Hurry!
[CHICHI]
Papa! Go help.
Hmm.
[GOKU pants]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[CHICHI] Goku!
[GOKU groans]
I couldn't reach him!
The flames are rising.
He's... He's trapped!
--[VILLAGERS chatter]
--[CHICHI cries]
ChiChi, don't cry.
We have to do something!
Goku, try your Kamehameha Wave!
Right.
[GOKU grunts]
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
[CHICHI]
No, Goku, don't!
Hmm?
Why not?
The wave is just too strong.
You'll destroy the castle
while you're trying to save it,
just like Master Roshi
did, long ago!
[GOKU] Don't worry!
I'll only target the fire!
Ha!
--[GOKU] Ha!
--[CHICHI yelps]
--[VILLAGERS screaming]
--[VILLAGERS chatter]
--[CHICHI whimpers]
You did it!
[CHICHI whimpers]
--[CHICHI gasps]
--[GOKU] What! Not more flames!
They're rising!
I know!
Flying Nimbus!
Stay here. I'll be right back!
Faster!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
[OX KING panting]
It's chasing me!
Ox King! Where are you?
[GOKU grunts]
[screams]
[OX KING]
Goku!
[GOKU]
Heh?
[OX KING]
Up here!
Hey! I'll be right there!
Listen, the Bansho
fan's the only thing
that can put out these flames!
Huh? Bansho?
Ah...
Fan once, and it will
cause a fierce wind.
Fan twice, and it
will create a cloud.
Fan three times,
and it brings a downpour.
--[GOKU] Uh...
--[ROSHI] It's quite miraculous!
Master Roshi, he had
the fan on his island,
but he threw it away.
He said it was old!
[GOKU yelps, whimpers]
[OX KING]
Goku!
[GOKU]
Uh?
[OX KING]
You must find the Bansho Fan!
It's the only way
to save the castle!
[GOKU]
Uhh...
Hmm...
But where is it? Think!
I need...
Fortuneteller Baba!
She can help me!
[GOKU laughs]
Show yourself to Baba.
Ah-ah-choo! Uh.
Reveal to m-ah-choo!
Ah-choo! Ah-choo!
Show yourself to Baba. Ah-choo!
Reveal to me! Ah-choo!
Uhh...
Here is your Basho Fan.
Ah-ah-ah-choo!
What's wrong, Baba?
[coughs]
I caught my first
cold in 200 years.
I can find anything
with this crystal ball,
except for a good doctor.
[coughs]
Anything? So where's
the Bansho fan?
Look, fortune telling isn't
a science. It's an art.
Heed my psychic vibration.
Now show me your location.
What is your location?
[screams]
What is it?
[GOKU]
What do you see? Is it the fan?
Hmm.
It's an octagon.
[BOTH]
Octagon?
[BABA] Is there an echo?
Yes, an octagon.
[BABA sneezes]
I need a vacation. Huh?
What now? Do you
see something else?
Hmm.
The fan's location is
somewhere east of here.
--[GOKU] What do we do now?
--Heh.
You could go.
[GOKU]
You're right. Let's go!
Eh?
[GOKU, BABA grunt]
[CHICHI screams]
This is not my
idea of a vacation!
[BABA coughs]
[CHICHI groans]
[OX KING thinking]
Uh... It doesn't look good.
It's near here.
Let's go look!
[BABA screams]
Somebody save me!
Uh?
What's the matter, Goku?
It's Oolong!
Huh?
[GOKU]
Hey, Oolong!
Huh?
I'm surprised to see you.
Why are you here?
Who's Oolong? I'm Jasmine.
[GOKU laughs]
Who are you trying
to kid? It's me, Goku.
Goku?
Boy, uh, you're sure
in a funny mood.
Anyway, I'm not alone.
ChiChi, Baba, say hi to Oolong!
[GOKU laughs]
Ah! Jasmine!
[UNNAN]
What's all that racket, Jasmine?
I can't hear myself oink.
[yelps]
There are two Oolongs?
But how can that be?
I'm glad you're here Unnan.
Maybe you can help me out.
Tell this guy my name
is Jasmine, not Oolong!
[GOKU]
Uhh...
[UNNAN] Oolong. Oh, you
remember him don't you?
He was the kid who got kicked
out of the Southern kindergarten
for stealing a teacher.
He was the only one of
us who ever got expelled.
Oh, right I remember.
What a loser.
You mean you really
aren't Oolong?
You catch on quick. Your
parents must be very proud.
I've never felt so insulted! How
dare you compare me to that pig!
I'm the leading citizen
of Octagon Village.
Octagon Village.
Uh-well, this
must be the place!
Um, maybe you could help us.
We're looking for
the Bansho fan.
Bansho fan? Huh?
It's a magical fan.
There's no fan here by that
name. There is the Bansho Spa.
You mean the Bansho Spa exists?
The one which can
cure any sickness?
It's the biggest tourist
attraction in the village.
What a coincidence!
This may be a vacation
after all. Care to join me?
[BOTH grunt]
That pretty girl...
...in the spa!
[BOTH laugh]
Thanks, but there's not time.
I have to find the Bansho fan.
I don't have a second to waste.
I can't afford not to.
My cold would disappear
immediately if I sat in the spa!
--[BOTH groaning]
--[BABA] As my health increases,
so will my fortune
telling abilities,
making me more effective in
helping you locate the fan.
[BOTH gasp]
Uh-oh.
Don't you know a
guy who knew someone,
who had a friend that
thought they saw the fan?
--[UNNAN laughs]
--Oh... You're right, I forgot!
[UNNAN chuckles]
The Bansho Fan! Where is it?
[UNNAN, JASMINE grunt]
It's somewhere deep in a valley,
which lays far beyond
those mountains way,
way in the distance.
Really?
[JASMINE]
You bet!
This could be it!
I'll go check it out!
I'll go, too.
[BOTH groan]
No, I need you to stay here
and look after Baba,
since she's sick,
she may need some help.
Okay.
I'll be back.
I guess I'm... I'm just worried.
I want you to be safe.
But I realize I can't
follow you everywhere.
[BOTH moan]
Come on! Where are you?
That Bansho fan has
to be here someplace!
Uh?
[JASMIN, UNNAN laugh]
[JASMINE] Uh... This is where
you get prepared for your bath.
Take your time.
[UNNAN chuckles]
I didn't know it was an outdoor
spa. This could be embarrassing.
[CHICHI whimpers]
Loosen up. Live a little.
[UNNAN, JASMINE] We'll make sure
you have your complete privacy.
[BOTH chuckle]
We're true to our word.
That shack will give
her complete privacy.
But to be certain, we'll
have to keep an eye on her,
which will be easy with the
modifications we've made.
[BOTH chuckle]
This is strange.
I don't see a valley,
only mountains and forests.
[JASMINE]
Eww...
[UNNAN groans]
[UNNAN] From now on, I'm
sleeping with a light on.
[BOTH sigh]
[BABA] It feels wonderful
in here, ChiChi.
Aaah!
What are you waiting for, girl?
Goku.
[UNNAN groans]
Uh, come on! Get in!
Oh, please find the fan, Goku.
[grunting] Is that all
she thinks about?
There's no valley around here.
Nothing but sand.
This is just a waste of time.
You can worry yourself to death.
It won't help Goku
find the fan any faster.
Try the spa a few minutes.
What have you got to lose?
Yes, you're right.
I could us a hot bath.
[JASMINE]
Here we go!
Our own private show!
[PIG]
Down in front!
Uh? Ow!
[PIGS grunting]
Hey!
Now this looks like a valley!
[GOKU grunts]
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six... Seven. Eight!
It's an octagon! Eight sides!
Ah... I found it!
[JASMINE]
Stop pushing!
[PIGS grunting]
That's my foot you're
stepping on, pal!
[PIGS grunting]
[JASMINE chuckling]
[UNNAN]
Move over. What did I miss?
[PUGS chuckling, grunting]
--[rumbling]
--Huh?
[PIGS squealing, yelling]
[shrieks]
[CHICHI]
Goku, where are you?
Huh?
[GOKU]
What was that?
Uh...
[gasps]
It's here! The Bansho fan!
[laughing]
[GOKU thinking]
I found it!
--[UNNAN, JASMINE grunt]
--[CHICHI screams]
Get out of here!
[BOTH scream]
--Eh?
--[UNNAN, JASMIN scream]
[UNNAN, JASMINE grunt]
Hmm... Uh?
[BABA whimpers]
[BABA yelps]
Huh?
[UNNAN, JASMINE scream]
[BABA whimpers, yelps]
[CHICHI]
Huh? Oh?
[CHICHI whimpers]
Hmm? Goku.
Eh... I thought I'd
found the Bansho fan.
It was just a drain plug.
Uh? Huh.. Uh.
[CHICHI whimpers]
[GOKU]
Uh...
[CHICHI]
Goku!
Hey! Down here!
[CHICHI] Look! The
Bansho fan's over there!
Uh?
Huh?
[GOKU whimpers]
I get it!
Goku, it's a map that shows
us how to make the fan!
A map?
It's clear, except
for those symbols.
[JASMINE]
Help! Get us down!
[UNNAN, JASMINE groan]
Ah, I recognize it!
Hmm?
[GOKU]
Mm?
I've seen a similar diagram on a
poster at my brother's house.
Ah-ha-choo!
Uh...
Master Roshi has this?
Ye... ah-choo!
That's great!
Hmm...
Ah-choo!
[UNNAN, JASMINE grunting]
[UNNAN, JASMINE scream]
[UNNAN]
Ouch!
[NARRATOR] Goku and ChiChi's
search for the Bansho fan
leads them to Master
Roshi's island.
Will they find it in time
to save the Ox King's Castle?
Or will ChiChi's father and
wedding dress go up in flames?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!