[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[GOKU]
You rely... too much on tricks.
When you meet Tao, be sure
to tell him I sent you!
[NARRATOR]
As Goku fought Tien Shinhan,
Master Shen used
Chiaotzu's mental powers
to paralyze the young hero,
leaving him defenseless
against Tien's attack.
[SHEN thinking]
Now! You must do it now!
[NARRATOR] However,
Master Shen's deception
backfired once Tien
learned the truth,
and he was quickly dismissed
from the tournament
thanks to Master Roshi's
Kamehameha Wave.
[CROWD screams]
[NARRATOR] With the influence
of his corrupt master removed,
Tien renounced his
quest for vengeance
and recommitted
himself to the match,
vowing to defeat
Goku at all costs.
Goku met his
opponent's challenge
with steely resolve and
unwavering determination.
[NARRATOR]
In a bid to ensure success,
Tien Shinhan called upon the
Four Witches Technique...
The monstrous power promised
to lend him an extra
hand... two of them.
[GOKU yelps]
[CROWD gasping]
Big trouble.
Big, big arms!
[CROWD gasping]
Oh, my!
As impossible as it may seem,
ladies and gentlemen,
what you are witnessing
is not an illusion.
Yes! Tien Shinhan has four arms!
You ready?
I guess so. I've never
fought four arms!
Don't worry.
This won't take long.
[yells]
[yelps]
[shrieks]
[BULMA sighs]
[yelps]
[yells]
Ow...
It's like... It's like having
to fight two enemies.
[GOKU groans]
[yelps]
[sighs]
[yells]
[laughs]
--[GOKU] Yaaaaaaah!
--[gasps]
[yelps]
[laughs]
Goku!
[GOKU grunts]
[laughs]
It's all downhill from here!
[screams]
[GOKU yelping]
[shrieks]
Goku!
Go, Tien!
[screaming]
[laughs]
Uh?
You have my hands and legs,
but you forgot about my tail!
[groans]
[groaning]
[ANNOUNCER] Using his tail,
Goku has forced Tien to let go!
A bold move!
You... Your tail packs
quite a sting.
I can't beat four arms, so...
I'll try eight.
[gasps]
[GOKU grunting]
He... can't do that... can he?
[gasping]
[OOLONG]
This is getting serious!
Tada!
[gasps]
Am I dreaming?
If you see eight arms,
you're not dreaming!
Stay with me, folks,
but we now have two
opponents in the ring
with 12 arms between them!
[laughs]
Is anyone else as disturbed
about this as I am?
[TIEN groans]
[yells]
[CROWD gasps]
What an awesome clash!
Goku!
Tien!
Oh, no!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
Both opponents have collapsed!
[KRILLIN]
Goku, no! Wake up!
[LAUNCH]
Quit loungin' around!
Okay... One... two...
[ROSHI thinking] This scene
looks eerily familiar.
[CROWD cheering]
Three...
Four...
...and five...
Six...
Get up! Hurry!
What's wrong with you?!
[ANNOUNCER]
Seven...
It's getting close...
Eight!
Yeah!
With only one count to spare,
both sides have
risen to their feet.
The match will continue!
[OOLONG] Cheer all you want.
This pig's nose is off limits!
[panting]
You look tired.
I'm feeling great!
[ANNOUNCER]
And resume!
They look rough... and tired.
[RADIO VOICE]
We now bring you back live
to the World Martial
Arts Tournament!
[CROWD cheering]
[yells]
[TIEN groans]
[GOKU laughs]
[CROWD gasps]
Goku has executed a
successful pinching move
and now has Tien Shinhan
subdued by his ankles!
[TIEN, GOKU grunting]
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER] Tien gains leverage
in this tense stand-off!
Who will be able to
hold out the longest?
Let go!
That's it!
Just hold your breath!
I suggest you let go
unless you wanna suffocate!
I'm okay.
Goku's in trouble!
No!
[yells]
Tien just gave up!
How come?
Perhaps he realizes the
futility of their struggle,
or maybe it's the pain.
[yells]
No mercy!
Show some nerve, Tien Shinhan!
Could you tell the
audience how you feel?
My legs are pulled
from their sockets!
How do you think I feel?
I can help, Tien.
No, Chiaotzu!
I told you, no interference!
Okay...
[yelping]
[yells]
[KRILLIN, ROSHI yelp]
No! Goku!
[ROSHI]
Krillin!
Yes, sir.
Nice one!
Tien has...
has escaped Goku's snare
and buried his opponent
in a pile of rubble!
[GOKU grunting]
Goku!
You're strong.
That's obvious.
Thanks for the stretch.
I'm feeling much better...
Should you get tired of losing,
you'd make a great
chiropractor...
[TIEN laughs]
What's a chiropractor?
You were born to fail.
The same as all those
who've come before you.
I cannot be defeated... Ever.
Why?
I no longer wish to kill you.
When the time comes, avoid it!
Huh?!
What's he talking about, Master?
He couldn't...!
The Tri-Beam Cannon!
Don't, Tien, don't!
It's madness. No, Tien Shinhan,
you must not do this!
Are you okay?
[panting]
No. That boy's going
too far this time!
What's going too far, Master?
The Tri-Beam Cannon...
A terrible technique.
With such devastating
power, it rivals...
...even the Kamehameha Wave!
To wield its lethal force is
to flirt with annihilation.
For all its advantages,
it demands a mighty toll,
leaving its master exhausted
to the point of death.
Even if you survive, your life
is shortened with each use.
[CHIAOTZU thinking]
Please stop this, Tien!
[TIEN thinking] I know
what I'm doing, Chiaotzu.
No need to worry. I won't
deplete all my energy.
Incredibly, Tien Shinhan
is levitating!
Kids, don't try this at home.
Tien, think this through!
This amazing move by
Tien Shinhan is unprecedented!
Don't panic,
ladies and gentlemen,
but if you haven't already,
I advise you to duck!
Goku! You cannot escape!
No problem. I don't
plan on going anywhere!
This is no time to be stubborn!
Goku, you've got to
get out of the ring!
Be careful, Tien!
I'm glad I've got a shell!
I hope you've got
room in there for two!
Goku...
But, Master, why would
Tien Shinhan use a technique
that could destroy
his own life.
Wouldn't that defeat
the purpose of winning?
[GOKU] I don't know what
you're planning to do,
but get on with it.
I can take it!
Ambition seldom gives
way to reason, my boy...
Tien would gladly forfeit
his life for honor.
[KRILLIN]
That's crazy!
So long!
[yelling]
His hands are starting to glow!
He's drawing the power of
his life force into them.
That doesn't look good.
Focus... the platform.
[TIEN thinking] I have to use
enough force to wipe him out.
But if I use too much energy,
it's all over.
This has to be perfect.
Tri Beam!
Goku, move!
Tien!
Look out!
[yells]
[CROWD screams]
Are you all right?
What happened?
[yelps]
Where's the platform?!
[CROWD gasping]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies and
gentlemen, please remain calm.
Everything is under control.
The fight will continue, uh,
assuming we can find the stage.
I was wrong to judge
my wave against this.
There's no comparison!
[KRILLIN] If the stage
is gone, what about--
Goku? Goku!
[KRILLIN]
Goku! Goku, where are you?!
[ROSHI thinking]
I've lost him.
[panting]
[NARRATOR] Like the stage
he was standing on,
Goku has disappeared
without a trace.
What is the fate
of our young hero?
Will Tien be crowned the
new Martial Arts Champion?
Find out when the
tournament concludes,
next time on Dragon Ball!