[NARRATOR] The greatest
of all teachers is life.
Three years ago, Master Roshi
sent his finest student, Goku,
out into this school
of experience.
His studies are
coming along nicely.
Oh, boy! There's my lunch!
[engine revs,
tires squeal]
[whimpers, gasps]
[BOAR] HA! HA! Now we got you!
Thought you could
get away from us, huh?!
You can't escape that way!
[GORILLA] Where do you
think you're going?
[BOAR] Where'd that
little runt go?!
[whimpers]
[yells]
--[BOAR] That's him there.
--[TIGER] Is he alive?
[laughs]
Rise and shine!
Time for your beating!
[TIGER] Mmm...
beatings for breakfast!
[GREEN FOX] Ow...
Please forgive me...! Ow!
Help! Help!
[GORILLA] Here's the juice!
Sorry it's pulped!
[GOKU] Stop!
[growls]
[GORILLA] Ooh! I hate it when
people interrupt breakfast!
[TIGER] Some folks
have no manners.
[TIGER chuckles]
[growls]
Buzz off! This
doesn't concern y--!
[yells]
[BOTH yelling]
[grunting]
--[TIGER] Let's get outta here!
--[BOAR] He's a monster!
[GORILLA] Mommy!
[sighs]
Oh, thank you, brother!
[NARRATOR] Face front, students!
Life class is in session.
Today's lesson: things aren't
always what they seem!
[GREEN FOX] My name's Konkichi.
Eat all you want there, Brother.
[GOKU] Thanks,
but my name's not "Brother."
It's Goku!
You saved my life!
Tell me a better reason
to call somebody "brother"!
Well, don't forget, you were a
big help to me too, Konkichi.
I mean, I really had no idea how
to even get to Papaya Island.
Aw, come on, taking
you to the airport
is the least I can do, Brother.
Airport? Wow!
You mean I'm actually gonna get
to ride around on an airplane?!
Of course you have to
take a plane, silly!
The World Martial
Arts Tournament
is tomorrow, isn't it?
Yeah.
Then you'll have to
take an airplane.
There's no other way
to get there on time.
I was just going
to run there.
I thought it'd be good training.
Hmm... Oh, I get it!
You're just kidding me!
Come on, you know you can't
run to an island, Brother!
[GOKU] I can't? Well,
thanks... uh... "brother."
Excuse me, but when's the
next flight to Papaya Island?
[FEMALE CLERK 1]
It's scheduled for three o'clock
this afternoon.
And after that?
That one's six o'clock
tomorrow evening.
Tomorrow?
Well, then I guess we're
gonna have to take
the three o'clock flight.
How's that for good fortune?
It looks like we
got here just in time.
How much is the ticket?
That'll be 15,000 Zeni
for one person.
Okay, Brother, let me
see your money.
My money?
Unless you know a
better way to pay for it.
[PILOT] Passengers,
we're about to experience
some rough weather.
[chuckles nervously]
Stop kidding around,
Brother. C'mon!
I don't have any
money, "brother."
You been traveling all
this time without any money?!
Yeah.
Then how did you
eat and sleep?!
I don't get it.
How does money help you
eat and sleep?
[KONKICHI yells]
[PILOT] Please buckle up
for a crash landing.
It wasn't a joke...
You were really going to try
to get there by running...
Sure was.
Oh man, for someone
who's traveled so much,
you sure don't know
your geography, do you?
[GOKU] Hmm?
Okay, lesson one:
Papaya Island is all the way on
the on other side of the world!
There's no way
you can run there!
But don't you worry.
I'll take care of all this.
Where are you going?
[KONKICHI] Back in a second!
[FEMALE CLERK 2] Ok, that's
two tickets to Papaya Island.
You'll need to be at the
boarding gate thirty minutes
before the three
o'clock take off time.
Well, we've got
some time to kill.
Let's go get some coffee.
[grunts]
--Oh!
--Well, excuse me, sir!
[yells]
[OFFICER] Hmm?
Say! You okay, little guy?!
Great! Wonderful!
You keep up the good work there,
officer! Heh-heh...
[KONKICHI thinking] I don't
think he suspects anything.
Just play it cool, Konkichi.
Whoops! Look at this!
Somebody dropped their tickets!
It'd sure be sad if
someone missed their flight
to Papaya Island.
[MAN 1] Our tickets!
Someone's stolen our tickets!
[OFFICER] Are these
your tickets, sir?
Lucky thing they turned up.
Yes, do you know who found them?
This young man...
Wait a minute...
he was just here.
Where'd he run off to?
--Hey!
--C'mon, Brother!
Let's go! Hurry!
Hmm... That boy... I wonder...
Hmm...
What's up, Brother?
We're going into town.
We've only got an hour
and a half to make 30,000 zeni!
Otherwise, this trip is gonna be
cut pretty short, Brother!
Uh... Thirty thousand?
But I thought the tickets
only cost fifteen?
Wait a minute! Are you
planning on going without me?
I get it! Thirty thousand
for both of us!
[GOKU] That sounds like
a lot of zeni!
Are you sure we can
get that much?
[KONKICHI] You'll see,
Brother, you'll see...
[CROWD murmuring]
[GOKU] Wow!
Look at all the colors!
[KONKICHI] It's just a carnival.
Haven't you ever
been to a carnival?
[GOKU] Not yet.
Can we make money here?
[KONKICHI] With your strength,
my friend, we can't lose!
So, how are we gonna
make money, Konkichi?
Trust me. Follow my lead.
[wails]
Don't cry, little boy...
I'll get your balloon for you.
Hang on.
There you go.
Oh, thank you!
[PARROT] Who's a pretty bird?
Who's a pretty bird?
--Hello! Hello!
--[BOY wails]
--Who's a pretty bird?
--[KONKICHI groans]
[wails]
Hey, kid, do you
like candy?
Here! Look at me little boy!
There's a smile!
Have fun now!
Thank you, mister!
You sure are good
with kids, Brother.
Aw, It's nothing.
They're easy.
[growls]
[CROWD] Awww...
Aw, that's too bad tough guy!
But everybody's a winner!
Be sure and pick up your
token prize on the way out!
Guaranteed not to fall apart
until you get home!
Who's next? Ring the bell
and win 50,000 zeni!
Step right up!
Don't be shy! Come on!
Who's it gonna be?
Huh? Who's next?
[KONKICHI] Oh! Oh! Over here!
My brother's next!
[BARKER] Three zeni, please!
[KONKICHI] Here you go.
Good luck.
So, all I gotta do to win the
money is ring that bell?
That's it, Brother.
Then the money is all ours.
[BARKER chuckles]
Hah! You see, folks,
not even a child's afraid to
play this game!
Step right up,
ladies and gentlemen!
I don't think I'm gonna use
the hammer on this, Konkichi.
What?!
Are you crazy, kid?!
What're you gonna do?!
Use you bare hands
or something? Come on!
Sure, why not. The hammer
will just get in the way.
[grunts]
Haaah...!
[gasping]
[GOKU thinking]
Well, that was easy.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
That shouldn't ring!
I rigged it myself...!
Fifty thousand zeni, please!
11... 12... 13... 14...
15... 16... 17... 18...
--19... 20... 21... 22... Huh?!
--[BABA] Is that you, Goku?
Well, hex my head
and call me the good fairy!
It IS you! How have
you been the last three years?
Oh, great!
I learned a lot!
Wonderful!
I know that all your friends
are looking forward to tomorrow.
Yeah? Me too!
I can't wait to see everybody!
I've really missed them!
Brother, who is this woman?
Oh, uh, sorry, Brother,
this is Baba.
She's one of the
greatest tattle-tellers
in the whole world.
Fortuneteller! The world's
greatest fortuneteller!
Oh, yeah! Fortuneteller!
Sorry 'bout that.
World's greatest!
Wow, that's something!
My name is Konkichi.
I'm just a nobody.
But any friend of Goku's
a friend of mine.
It's a pleasure
to meet you Baba.
You must be really great,
if my brother says you are.
Goku? What's all this
"brother" business?
Oh, see I saved Konkichi's
life and ever since
he said we should call
each other brother.
Yeah, well... I guess
it's just not safe
for us law-abiding
citizens any more.
Ohh...? Really?
Uh... yeah... um...
So why were those three guys
chasing you in the first place?
Uh... Three guys...?
How'd you...?
[KONKICHI thinking] She knows!
I don't know how, but she knows!
Uh, hey, how about something
to drink there, Brother?
No thanks. I'm not
thirsty right now.
Uhhh...
Nonsense! I mean,
you've had a busy day!
Mustn't get dehydrated,
you know?
Okay, but hurry
back, Konkichi!
[BABA] Mmmmm...
[CASHIER] Sorry, sir, you can't
have the Mushy Burger
without chili...
Okay, who ordered
the Slop Shake?
[CROWD murmuring]
There's something freaky
about that Baba character.
I can't put my finger on it,
but she knew all about me.
I don't wanna leave my brother,
but... she's gonna tell him!
I don't want him to find out--
[screams]
[grunts]
[KONKICHI] Oh, no...
Well... that's quite
a bankroll, Konkichi!
[growls]
It's almost half
what you owe us.
So where's the other half?
[BOAR] I say we
beat it outta him!
[TIGER] That wouldn't even
make a down payment.
[GORILLA] Wait, Konkichi
wants to go straight.
Let's give him
some responsibility.
[chuckling,
KONKICHI grunts]
I think it's time that you
earned your keep.
So, we've gotta little job
for you to do, Konkichi.
[OOLONG] Come on!
What's the hold up?
The plane's gonna take off
before we get there!
Hold on! We're still waiting
for Master Roshi!
Yoo-hoo, Master Roshi!
So, how do I look, baby?
Ooh, I think you look
very distinguished.
Distinguished...?
Darn, I was going for sexy.
Hurry up, old man!
Bulma, a-and this is just
hypothetical, mind you,
if you were walking down the
street and you saw me
wearing these cool threads,
would you be likely to say...
"Boy! He's hot!"
Oh, here we go again!
What in the world does it matter
how an old man looks?!
I swear, you ask the dumbest
questions, Master Roshi!
Now hurry up, would you,
or we're going to be late!
[LAUNCH] Well,
that's everything.
Have fun, everybody!
So, uh... you sure you
wouldn't like to go?
Oh no, the city air
is bad for my sinuses.
[ROSHI] Okay, Launch.
You take care of yourself.
You--
Ahh... Ah-choo!
[ALL gasp]
[LAUNCH] Sayyyy...
And just where do you
think you're going?!
We're just taking
a quick trip
to the World Martial Arts
Tournament, that's all.
And you were gonna
leave without me?
But didn't you say the city air
was bad for your sinuses?!
--[ALL scream]
--Nonsense!
I love a little smog
in my lungs!
I can't wait to
test my training!
Yamcha, won't Goku
be surprised
when he sees how much
we've improved?!
You think Goku
has changed much?
Nah. I wouldn't doubt that
he's just the same old Goku.
If I know Goku, he's
already on the island
checking out
the competition.
[GOKU] Konkichi sure has
been gone a long time.
[BABA] It doesn't take
that long to buy a soft drink.
I'm afraid something
may have happened to him.
Maybe you'd better
go look for Konkichi.
We only have forty minutes!
Sure. Be right back...
--[gunshots]
--Huh?!
[BOY] ♪ La la la la la la... ♪
[gunshots]
Run for your lives!
[sirens blare]
[KONKICHI gasps]
[DETECTIVE] You are
completely surrounded!
Drop your weapon!
I didn't do it! You gotta
believe me! I was framed!
I was a set up! I was!
Oh no! Why...? Why?!
[Konkichi?!
Ah...! Brother!
You gotta help me!
I didn't do anything, I swear!
Quiet you!
And get it in the car!
Mr. Officer, may I please
have a word with Konkichi?
Sorry, son, we gotta
take him in.
Aw, let the boy speak to
his brother for a minute.
His brother?! Please,
they look nothing alike!
[BABA chuckles]
I... guess a family
visit won't hurt.
Konkichi, are you a criminal?
Of course not, Brother!
You know me!
Well, then why--
I was framed! They set me up!
I wouldn't do
something like this!
You know I could
never rob a bank!
You believe me,
don't you, Brother?!
Huh?
Are you gonna stand
there and say that you didn't
pick-pocket those tickets
at the airport?
Konkichi, is this the truth?
[KONKICHI] Yes...
I'm sorry, Brother...
It's true...
I'm... really a bad little fox.
Always have been.
Even when I was a kid.
I never felt at home.
I just couldn't fit in anywhere.
I was orphaned at an early age
and I never knew any family.
That is, until I
met you, Brother.
You're the first family
I ever had...
[KONKICHI] All my life
I had to steal.
I never knew any other way.
But when you saved me, I thought
things could be different.
I finally knew what it was like
to have a brother.
And to be someone's
brother in return!
I don't think you should
call me brother anymore.
No. You're right.
I don't deserve
to be your brother.
Those guys did set me up,
but I was bad to begin with.
I really wanted to go
to school and learn a trade,
but I have no talents.
Even though I could
never be your brother,
I want you to know that
being with you has changed me.
I want you to know
I'm sorry for what I did.
Please, forgive me,
Goku! Please!
I forgive you!
Baba, you think could you tell
me where those bad guys went?
Of course, dear,
for a fee.
I don't have
any money,
But you'll be giving Konkichi a
chance to turn his life around.
Ha, ha...!
Great... Baba's Psychic
Charity Line...
Well, let's see here.
[BABA] They're headed south
in a yellow car.
[GOKU] Be right back!
[KONKICHI] Goku!
[laughing]
[That was easy!
Yeah! Konkichi gets the blame,
we get the money!
[GOKU] Pull over!
Who's that?!
[yelling]
[BOAR] It's that tough kid!
Let's see how tough he is
filled with of bullets!
[gasping]
Humph! You're not going to
stop me that way!
[squealing]
[yells]
[yelling]
[screaming]
Let that be
a lesson to you!
Oh no! Is that my...?
Terrific, I just
missed my airplane!
[KONKICHI] Thank you...
Thank you so much, Goku.
You're welcome, Konkichi.
[KONKICHI sobs]
[BOY] Mister!
Huh...?
You're the kid with the balloon!
Are you sad?
Wha...?
This will make you happy!
Happy...?
Yeah!
Konkichi, my friend...
You sure make a good teacher!
Imagine! Ha ha! Me, a teacher.
[BOY giggles]
[BOTH laugh]
[BABA] Papaya Island is way on
the other side of the world...
that way.
I guess I'll swim!
What?! Are you really
going to swim there?
Sure am. Why not?
I don't have any other choice.
[KONKICHI] Wow!
[GOKU] Bye, Brother!
"Brother"?
[BABA] Well, you gotta
love that kid.
[KONKICHI] Goku,
I'm going back to school!
I'm gonna be
the best teacher ever!
I'll make you proud, Brother!
[NARRATOR] Goku leaves his
newfound friends behind
as he desperately
attempts to make
the trans-ocean journey to the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
It's a race against time
for our young hero.
Will he be able to catch up
to Master Roshi and the others?
Or will he be forced
to sit this one out?
[NARRATOR] And even if Goku
does reach the tournament,
he'll be faced with the
fiercest competition
in his fighting career...
You don't want to miss the next
thrill-packed chapter
in the Dragon Ball Saga!