[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
the countdown to victory began
with Goku poised to win the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
However, Junior put
a hole in Goku's plan
by bouncing back
with a surprise attack
that nearly destroyed
the young hero.
[CHICHI]
You monster!
[NARRATOR] As Junior
prepared to stamp Goku out,
his friends came to the rescue.
Unfortunately, they failed.
But, they were able to distract
the sinister warrior long
enough for Goku to recover.
[GOKU] Good thing you aim
as bad as you fight!
You missed my vital organs.
All of them?
[NARRATOR] Junior was shocked
by Goku's declaration
to continue the match.
It was clear to both opponents
that this fight had become
a matter of life or death.
And now, the final confrontation
to determine the real
master of martial arts!
[growling]
[grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[groans]
[roaring]
[GOKU screams]
[ALL shriek]
[GOKU groans]
[panting]
[groaning]
[PICCOLO JR.growls]
[GOKU pants]
[laughing]
[panting]
[lauging]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[panting]
[laughing]
[pants]
[PICCOLO JR.]
After all the hard work
I put into renovating
this place,
the least you could do is
stop leaking on the floor.
[groans, pants]
Watch out, Goku!
Uhh?
[roaring]
[screams]
[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[GOKU shrieks]
--[GOKU screams]
--[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[GOKU groans]
[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[GOKU gasps]
--[GOKU shrieks]
--[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[screaming]
He broke his leg!
--[GOKU sputters]
--[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
That's it. I can't
watch any more of this!
--[GOKU groans]
--[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR.]
I'd just like to thank you.
Seeing you lying in
the dirt, writhing in pain
means more to me than you
could possibly imagine.
[GOKU sputters]
[laughing]
[GOKU screams]
[PICCOLO JR.] My father lost
much during his last battle,
including his left arm.
Goku!
[KAMI gasps]
Allow me to extend you the
same courtesy you gave him.
[BOTH whimper]
Oh, no!
[GOKU whimpers]
[PICCOLO JR.] All right.
I won't take your arm,
but you get the idea.
I've deprived you of
the use of your body.
[GOKU groans]
And now, Goku, I will
deprive you of your life.
[GOKU groans]
--[OOLANG whimpers]
--[PUAR shrieks]
[BOTH whimper]
H-He's going to kill Goku!
He doesn't care
about the tournament.
He just wants to win!
Didn't you hear what I said!
We can't just stand by
and let this happen.
[GOKU groans]
[ALL whimpering]
This has gone far
enough! Please stop!
Tien Shinhan, isn't it?
Uh?
You can save Goku
if you kill me.
What?
Junior will die, too.
--We can't hurt you, Kami.
--Yeah!
What are you waitin' for?
He's right, kill him!
Uhh...
You must hurry...
before it's too late.
[TIEN grunts]
Tien, I cannot destroy myself.
If you want to save him,
this may be your only chance.
But... I can't!
My demise does not
have to be permanent.
Once Junior is destroyed,
you can ask for the Eternal
Dragon to resuscitate me.
There's no time to waste.
[TIEN grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[KAMI]
Tien Shinhan?
[grunts]
Okay, I will do it.
[BOTH gasp]
[KAMI]
Hmm... Hmmm...
[TIEN grunts]
[GOKU]
Don't do it!
Uh?
[KAMI]
Huh?
[GOKU]
That's... It's not necessary!
[TIEN gasps]
[KAMI gasps]
[GOKU groans]
I know I can win!
Are you sure you can beat him?
No! You can't even move.
That's just impossible!
He is right, Goku!
You don't have a chance!
[TIEN grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[GOKU whimpers]
[roaring continues]
Too late!
[BOTH scream]
[GOKU groans]
--[GOKU whimpers]
--[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[GOKU yelps]
[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[KRILLIN, TIEN yell]
Relax and enjoy your death.
You have nowhere else to go!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PUAR, OOLANG scream]
[LAUNCH, BULMA scream]
[CHICHI]
No!
[GOKU whimpers]
[GOKU yelps, whimpers]
[CHICHI yells]
[ALL groaning, yelping]
[KRILLIN yells]
[BOTH scream]
--[YAMCHA grunts]
--[CHICHI screams]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR. pants]
[BOTH groan]
--[LAUNCH groans]
--[BULMA groans, yelps]
[PICCOLO JR. pants]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[KAMI whimpers]
[KAMI gasps]
[ALL groan]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR.] It's done! It's
too bad you were obliterated.
I would like to have kept
some of you as a souvenir!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[CHICHI]
Uhh... Is he--
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
I've won! Goku is no more!
The world is now mine
to do with what I will!
A new age will soon
dawn on the Earth!
One marked by suffering, pain,
and torment for all humankind!
Goku! I never thought I'd be
a widow before I was a bride!
[CHICHI cries]
--[OOLANG grunts]
--[PUAR coughs, yelps]
You're gonna pay for this!
It's a pity. Goku deserved
better than this.
Ohh...
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
There's no need to grieve
for your fallen companion.
You'll be joining him shortly.
[BOTH scream]
--[KRILLIN grunts]
--Monster!
You can all keep Goku
company in the afterlife.
[TIEN, KRILLIN, YAMCHA grunt]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[KRILLIN pants]
Ah?
[whimpers]
What's the matter?
[KRILLIN]
Up above! Isn't that--?
[TIEN grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
--[KAMI] Uhh.. Ah...
--[ROSHI gasps, laughs]
Goku!
[PICCOLO JR.]
Huh?
Well, look who's coming back!
[yelps]
[ROSHI]
Ehh...
[yelps]
[BOTH]
Do it, Goku!
[GOKU]
I told you I'd win!
[PICCOLO JR. screams]
--[GOKU yells]
--[PICCOLO JR. screams]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO JR.]
Uh...
--[PICCOLO JR. groans]
--[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[GOKU]
Was it far enough?
Huh?
Is he outside-ohh...
the ring?
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[ANNOUNCER]
There's not much left.
[GOKU]
Can you tell? Have I won?
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
Well... uh, it appears
Junior is out of bounds.
The winner of the 23rd World
Martial Arts Tournament is Goku!
[GOKU laughs]
--[KRILLIN] All right!
--[ROSHI] Fantastic!
[BOTH laugh]
[LAUNCH, PUAR, CHICHI, YAMCHA,
KRILLIN] Yeah! You did it! Yeah!
[YAJIROBE grunts]
It's about time! Is it
safe to come out now?
Good work! Boy,
you look terrible.
You're safe now.
How do you feel?
My body's numb and
my head's pounding.
But, other than that,
I feel great.
[YAJIROBE groans]
[ROSHI] Funny, they never look
psychotic when they're sleeping.
[KAMI]
Hmm...
[YAJIROBE]
Do you have plans for Junior?
[BULMA, CHICHI,
YAMCHA, KRILLIN gasp]
[YAJIROBE]
I'm hungry.
Yajirobe! What about your beans?
I want some real food.
You want beans? Here.
Have a bean buffet.
Ah, thank you! Ahh.
[GOKU chews]
[ALL gasp, whimper]
[GOKU groans]
[YAJIROBE grunts]
--[GOKU laughs]
--[CHICHI giggles]
[GOKU grunts]
Ah. Hah.
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU]
Woohoo! I did it! I've won!
Yes! I'm the champion!
Yeah-ha-ha! Woohoo! Yeah!
Ha-ha. He-he. I won! I won!
[CHICHI] I've never
seen him so happy!
I didn't know those beans could
heal you as well as fill you up.
Yeah well, I still
can't understand
why they taste like fish.
[GOKU]
I won! Yeah-ha!
Amazing.
[KAMI]
Mhm... hmm...
Yeah!
Uh? Huh?
[KAMI groans]
Ah...
No, Kami!
[KAMI]
No more.
[KAMI grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
No!
[KAMI]
Huh?
Get out of my way!
No, first tell me what
you're planning to do.
[KAMI grunts]
[KAMI]
He is still alive!
You know the danger he poses.
This world will never be safe
until he stops breathing.
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
Pure evil can never be tamed.
But if he dies,
you'll go with him.
There has to be another
option besides destroying him.
I've already explained to you
that destroying me won't matter.
You can ask the Eternal Dragon
to bring me back again.
Kami is right, Goku.
Trust him. His plan will work.
But you're Kami. Are you
capable of telling a lie?
Say what?
The Eternal Dragon
and Dragon Balls
were created by Kami, right?
[KAMI grunts]
So, then it's safe to assume
that if Kami is destroyed,
the Dragon Balls will
disappear as well, correct?
[KAMI]
Ohh...
What's that?
[ROSHI]
Ehh...
[KAMI]
Hmm.
Hmm...
Sometimes, even I
will make a mistake.
I created this monster.
Yet, he's become so powerful
as to surpass even me,
plunging the world into chaos!
I've lost more than power.
I've lost my perspective.
I no longer deserve to
govern this or any world.
How can you say such
things, when it was you
who brought our
world peace again?
If not for your training,
Goku would never have attained
the level of skill he has now.
Junior would have won.
And if the Dragon Balls
hadn't been forged,
none of these young warriors
would have ever met.
And I can't begin to count
the number of people
who owe their lives
to these kids.
When their quest began,
they were just children.
But they soon grew into heroes.
Yeah!
When the world needed saving,
eight kids answered the call.
One ball, that's
how it all began.
Goku, you're fortunate to have
had such an excellent teacher.
[GOKU]
Mh-hm.
No one is more wise or as goofy.
--[ROSHI] Mhm?
--[TIEN laughs]
No, no. Really, I just
taught him a few basic skills.
I couldn't have raised them
into such fine warriors
without the aid of you
and Master Korin. Heh...
[BOTH laugh, gasp]
[GOKU]
Uhh...
--[KAMI grunts]
--[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU laughs]
Wear the symbol of
the turtle with pride.
Never forget where
you came from.
[GOKU]
Thank you.
Yajirobe, can I have
another Senzu bean?
[YAJIROBE grunts]
If you keep eating like this,
you're gonna get fat! Here!
Thanks.
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
Eat up.
--[ROSHI] No! Don't.
--[KAMI] Goku!
[KAMI]
What're you doing?
Stop! Are you crazy?
We don't wanna wake him up!
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
Ah! Ah... Ah.
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[ALL yelp]
That's just great! Maybe you
two can become best friends!
Goku!
[GOKU] My reason for
helping you is simple.
If I destroyed you,
Kami would suffer as well.
Besides, without a
rival to fight,
I wouldn't have much to do. You
seem to fit that role nicely.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
You're a moron if you
think this changes
anything between you and I.
Mercy is a loathsome trait,
and you will soon learn
that I have no such weakness.
When that glorious day arrives,
the whole world will be mine!
[ROSHI thinking]
He will never stop.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Let's just hope between now
and then he discovers a hobby!
[PICCOLO JR.]
I'll see you real soon.
Until then, I'll see you
in your nightmares!
[GOKU thinking]
When that day comes,
I hope you're not
too disappointed.
I've beaten you once.
And I'll do it again.
[BULMA thinking]
It's difficult to believe
that little boy I found in
the woods all those years ago
is now a martial arts champion.
I can't wait to see
what he does next.
[CHICHI]
Goku! You did it!
You did it! You're so brave!
--[GOKU gasps]
--[CHICHI] And you're alive!
I'm so proud of you! Oh...
Easy, easy! ChiChi, please,
not in front of everyone!
He-he. You've just
discovered the one thing
you'll never be able to
defeat. Love conquers all.
Good work. Oh, and, Tien,
are you expecting a visitor?
What? Hey!
[ALL]
Uh?
[CHIAOTZU]
Tien!
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
[TIEN]
Chiaotzu! You're alive!
--[GOKU chuckles]
--[KAMI] Goku.
[GOKU]
Uh?
You've proven yourself
worthy. In fact, I'd like
to offer you my job.
Uh? Me? Are you serious?
Mh-hm. I have the utmost
confidence in you.
It could be your
greatest adventure.
No, no, no, no, no! I couldn't.
I appreciate your
confidence in my abilities,
but that's not the
adventure I'm looking for.
It's your job, keep it!
Don't be hasty.
Think of all the good you
could do with that power!
You are the only one I
could trust to succeed me.
What do you say?
[GOKU laughs]
[KAMI gasps]
[GOKU]
Flying Nimbus!
--[GOKU] Heh. Let's go!
--[CHICHI giggles]
Sorry, Kami! But it doesn't
get any better than this!
[ALL]
Goodbye, Goku!
[KRILLIN, ROSHI laugh]
[CHICHI laughs]
Hmm... I guess this is the end.
[ROSHI yelps]
[ROSHI]
Oh-ho... That... stings.
[NARRATOR]
No one can say
what tomorrow will
bring for our heroes.
But one thing is certain,
wherever adventure exists,
Goku will be there!