[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Yamcha and Krillin
pulled out all the stops
and threw the
competition for a loop
with their impressive
fighting styles.
Not to be outdone,
Tien proved deft
in vanquishing his opponents.
Goku gave King Chapa a serious
workout during their battle.
[NARRATOR] While Jackie Chun
kicked things into overdrive.
All together,
the Elimination Round
of the 22nd World
Martial Arts Tournament
proved to be an intense,
action-packed extravaganza
of fighting prowess
and iron-will.
[NARRATOR] One after another,
the competitors fought...
and fell...
to the might of our heroes.
[NARRATOR] But good didn't
always triumph over evil.
Darkness was a breath away
from enveloping all.
[CROWD murmuring]
No one's allowed
in the Great Hall--
I don't care whose
sister's mother's brother's
cousin you are!
I'm telling ya,
odds favorite is number forty.
Oolong.
Have you had any luck
in spotting Master Roshi?
[OOLONG] I haven't seen anything
but sunspots for an hour!
He's here somewhere.
Let's split up.
[OOLONG] Fine!
Puar and I will find him!
[PUAR] We'll track him down!
[CROWD cheering]
[chattering, murmuring]
[singing]
I'm excited to be
fighting in the finals,
but it's gonna be
a little weird
if we have to fight each other.
[YAMCHA] Yeah...
I guess so, Krillin.
[TIEN laughs]
I don't know how you do it.
I don't think I could
do what you do;
survive on blind luck.
It's a shame you don't have
any real skills of your own.
[scoffs]
You're the lucky one, bozo.
You've only gotten this far
because you haven't
fought me yet.
[huffs] Poor Yamcha...
Only thing more
pathetic than a loser
is a loser who thinks
he's born to win.
[growls, gasps]
What are you looking at?
Come on, speak if you've
got something to say!
Uh!
Baldy.
Uh! Have you looked
in the mirror lately?!
You're not exactly
sporting a lion's mane, pal!
You're wrong.
That's it?!
You've only got one hair,
ya pasty unicorn!
That's better than none.
Chiaotzu, stop it.
You know you're supposed
to keep that hat on.
You'll catch a cold.
--[CHIAOTZU] Nnnaaahhh...
--[KRILLIN] Don't laugh at me!
[GOKU singing]
[OOLONG] Master Roshi?!
[PUAR] Master Roshi!
Where are you?!
Hm... Hmmm?
[OOLONG] Move.
[GIRL] Huh?
[OOLONG] I've got you now!
Roshi!
Master?
[screams]
[OOLONG]
I know you're--oops!
[OOLONG] Gotcha!
[screams]
[chuckles, yells]
Ow! Hey! What was that for?
[BULMA] Why would Master Roshi
be in the girls' washroom?
Well?
[OOLONG] I told you.
I thought it was the boys!
I'm so sure.
I was trying to
be nice and help out,
but all I get is flak!
I don't need this abuse!
Stop yelling!
It was your fault!
You're as bad as Master Roshi!
You should have gone with him!
[grunts] I wish!
What if Master Roshi
isn't hiding?
What if something
happened to him?
I hope he's all right.
[bird cawing]
[SHEN] Hello ladies. I heard
you lost a turtle in the crowd.
I hope no one stepped on him.
[chuckles]
That isn't funny.
If that was an attempt at
some cleverly veiled threat,
you failed miserably!
You'd better not have had
anything to do with this.
[clears throat]
I'm in the dark the same as you.
Enough of this!
I'm done looking!
Come on, life's
too short to be sour.
I'll find him for you.
[BULMA and OOLONG gasp]
[YAMCHA] I'm serious.
You should have seen his face.
I was like, "Hey, look buddy,
you better fight me
or hand over the jewel,
either way you're gonna lose."
[ROSHI] What a waste.
Shen's hoodlum tendencies seep
through everything he touches.
Hello! Can you
hear me in the back?
Uh, participants,
please come forward.
[GOKU] Yeah. I am, too.
Hey, nice suit!
Yes, exquisite, isn't it?
I had it made custom.
--[GOKU] Neat.
--[ANNOUNCER] Nice to see
the new generation taking
an interest in good taste.
Fighters will be paired off
in the same fashion
as in the Elimination Round.
When your name is called,
please step forward
and draw a number from the box.
Listen loud, people.
First up, Jackie Chun.
Yeah, yeah.
So the old man won
the Championship last time.
How exciting.
Let's see how he fares
against an average opponent.
[MAN WOLF grumbles]
Sounds like someone
has a score to settle.
You have it in for Jackie Chun?
Hey, buddy. Stay out of it.
I think we just found
the perfect volunteer
to fight the old geezer,
don't you, Chiaotzu?
Yes.
Looks like my number is four.
[ANNOUNCER] You're going
to fight the second match...
Next up is Yamcha.
Right.
This one belongs to me.
Got it?
Yep.
Number one.
[ANNOUNCER] Very well, you will
be fighting the first match.
Next, Pamput, please.
Yes.
Mine is number seven.
You're in fight four.
Next, Tien.
You know what to do.
Yup.
[grunts]
Number two.
Hm.
[ANNOUNCER] All right...
That puts you fighting
Yamcha in match number one.
It's a shame you're not
gonna get past the first match,
Tell yourself whatever it
takes to get you in the ring,
but then you're mine.
[ANNOUNCER] Krillin?
Here!
[KRILLIN] I've got six.
Then you'll be fighting
in the third match.
Next up, Wolfman, step forward.
I'm not some two-bit sell-out!
My name is Man Wolf!
[MAN WOLF growls]
[ANNOUNCER stammers]
Pardon me.
You just see a hairball
and think we all look alike.
Wolf Men are poor,
cowardly creatures...
Men who become wolves
during a full moon!
[howl]
But Man Wolves...
We are different, transforming
from wolf to man...
by full moon.
Someone's overcompensating
for something.
Uh, I see.
Now that you mention it,
I can tell a difference.
Man Wolf, please draw.
[grumbles]
[ROSHI] Mmm?
[ROSHI] I hope he has a
better disposition in the ring.
[MAN WOLF] Three!
Thank you, Mr. Wolf.
That places you in match two,
where you will be
fighting Jackie Chun.
Jackie Chun!
That guy sounds
a little too anxious
if you ask me.
I feel sorry for Jackie.
I wonder if he
ever stops growling.
[ROSHI] Please let him
eat before the fight.
Kia... Chia...
ought... zoo... zooyou...
Chiazoo...
[CHIAOTZU] Chiaotzu.
[ANNOUNCER] Oh...
[clears throat]
Uh, please draw.
Five.
[ANNOUNCER] Number five.
You'll be fighting in
the third match against Krillin.
[KRILLIN laughs]
Come on!
You've gotta be kidding me!
What a joke!
That kid's no warrior.
Well, Goku, everyone else
is accounted for,
which means you're number eight.
That puts you fighting in the
fourth match against Pamput.
Uh...!
How can I be number eight
if I didn't draw a number?
Here goes.
[GOKU] Hey! You're right.
I'm number eight.
How did you know that?
Uh... Lucky, I guess.
[TIEN laughs]
Your Master Roshi
really picks his pupils
from the cream-of-the-crop,
doesn't he?
What's funny about wanting
to pick your own number?
Nothing. Be quiet, Chiaotzu.
All the fights
have been decided.
[ANNOUNCER] Match one
will have Yamcha fighting Tien.
[ANNOUNCER] The second match
will be Man Wolf
versus Jackie Chun.
The third match,
Kia-chia, uh, oat zoo...
[CHIAOTZU] Chiaotzu...
[ANNOUNCER] Versus Krillin!
[ANNOUNCER] And the fourth
and final match,
Pamput versus Goku.
Lastly,
when your name is called,
promptly enter the ring.
Are there any questions?
I anticipated you'd want
to feast before the fights,
so we're prepared
for you this time.
That's great!
[chuckles]
Are all your teammates
that "focused"?
[KRILLIN] At least we don't have
to compete against each other
in the first round of fights.
Heh, that's a relief.
[ROSHI] No, that's
a coincidence, but a good one.
It's amazing these fools
got this far.
They don't suspect a thing.
Not surprising,
but you did a good job.
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
Chiaotzu! Stop it!
[CROWD cheering]
Quite a crowd.
And I'll bet Master Roshi
is somewhere inside it, hiding!
He's up to something.
There's no reason for him
to be hiding from us.
That's true. Especially when
Launch got us such great seats!
What?
[KRILLIN] Maybe the rest
of you can find a good place
to catch the action.
[OOLONG] With Launch here,
anything is possible.
She's good at making room!
[KRILLIN and GOKU] Huh?
Follow me, boys.
My friend and I'll show you
the best seats in the house.
[ROSHI and KRILLIN
chuckle nervously]
All right, people, listen up!
I want this path
cleared out on the double!
Let's go! Move it!
[CROWD screaming, yelling]
[gunfire]
I did that?! I don't understand.
How is that possible?
I don't even like guns.
[BOTH] Uh...
Could've fooled me!
Oolong, do us all a favor
and take another look for Roshi?
[groans] But the match
is just about to start.
[SHEN] Don't worry...
I'm handling it.
In fact, I just
spoke with the sponsor.
What did you do?
[announcement tune plays]
[SPONSOR] Attention.
A family is asking for help
in locating their senile,
old-as-dirt grandfather.
Their words, folks, not mine.
He is described as
being short, fat, and bald.
This fits the description
of half the audience. Boy!
Oh! Did I say that on mic?!
Anyway, his family says
he closely resembles
an ugly turtle. He-heh.
So if you have any information
on his whereabouts,
please contact an official.
[announcement tune plays]
[GOKU]
Turtle? Sounds like Master.
[KRILLIN] That would be
too much of a coincidence,
don't you think?
The description does
sound a lot like Master Roshi.
Malarkey!
Master Roshi isn't fat!
[KRILLIN] Huh?
Oh! What's with you?!
That wasn't an accurate
description of Master Roshi.
He's not our grandfather!
I don't think
it's right to call him
a turtle! like that, man.
He-heh.
Don't blame the messenger.
I can't help it if all of
Roshi's qualities are bad.
Hm. He has got a point.
The old man is creepy.
Oolong!
[grunts]
[gong rings]
[ANNOUNCER] Welcome to the show!
I'm your host.
Are you ready for this?!
[OOLONG] Oh yeah!
We wanna see some action!
And now, the moment you've
all been waiting for,
the World Martial
Arts Championship!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER]
Many of you are looking at me
with those adorable,
clueless faces and saying,
"Hey, what's this all about?"
Some of you already know that
we started with 182 competitors
who came to vie for
the championship title
and the prize of
five hundred thousand zeni!
But that's ancient history!
Because the massive horde
has been whittled down
to eight finalists
who are appearing here today
to fight for you! That's right!
And I guarantee
the fights you're expecting
are going to be spectacular!
I've been waiting
to see this forever!
[SHEN] Enjoy it while it lasts.
It won't take long
for my team to win the title!
[chuckles]
Tell me something, Shen,
do you dream in color?
It's time to lay down the law!
Each match will proceed
without a time limit
and without interruption.
The fighter looses only if
he's thrown out, steps out,
or gets knocked out
for at least ten seconds!
[ANNOUNCER]
Without further delay,
the first match
begins right now
as Yamcha
battles Tien Shinhan.
Here we go!
[cheering]
Here they come!
Good luck, Yamcha!
You're looking at the person
who's gonna take you down.
You hearin' me, three eyes?
Oh? I didn't know
you had a sense of humor.
When you bring together
such talented warriors as these,
there are bound to be
some interesting stories.
In what will surely astound
trivia buffs for years,
nearly half of
today's competitors
are from the same house.
Yamcha is one of
three pupils representing
the Turtle Hermit, Master Roshi,
in the Championship Round.
Master's out there
somewhere... I hope.
[chuckles lightly]
Tien Shinhan represents the
Crane Hermit, Master Shen.
Judging by the reputations
of their instructors,
these warriors should
put on quite a show.
[ANNOUNCER] So now that
we all know each other,
what say we get to some action!
How's the view... baldy.
[KRILLIN growls]
Heh. Tien will beat him.
Shen will be sorry.
What's the big deal?
Why do y'all get so excited?
I said long ago,
these fights are fixed.
I was born to fight.
You have no idea
who you're messing with.
Does it matter?
I'm still going to win.
Now who has a sense of humor?
[CROWD cheering,
drums pounding]
[drums continue,
increasing tempo]
[gong crash]
[ANNOUNCER] Match one... begin!
[CROWD cheering]
I'll start off real slow, Tien.
You just try
and keep up with me.
Hmph! Do what makes you
feel good, Yamcha.
It's your funeral.
Oh, man! Yamcha's gonna
win this match easy!
I'm not so sure
it's going to be easy.
Tien's a good fighter.
I'd love some food.
I'm starving.
Die!
[KRILLIN] Huh?
Go Yamcha!
Fight your best, Yamcha!
You'll win!
[chuckles]
[grunts, chuckles]
[YAMCHA yells]
[bellows]
[TIEN grunts]
[chuckles]
[TIEN yells]
[yells]
[groans, yells]
[ANNOUNCER] Some extraordinary
moves by Yamcha,
which prove he can
really roll with the punches!
[grunts]
[TIEN grunts]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[CROWD murmurs]
Uh...
What a fight!
Uh-huh... This is exciting!
[ANNOUNCER]
Wow! That's all I can say!
What a breathtaking start
for the first fight!
Yamcha and Tien
seem evenly matched.
The result is unbelievable!
[YAMCHA thinking]
This guy is relentless!
I'm glad the crowd
is having fun.
[TIEN thinking] Looks like this
upstart wasn't just bragging.
He is good.
Perhaps I'll get
a little workout
at this competition after all.
Time's up! Wolf Fang
Blowing Wind Technique!
Heh. Sounds like fun!
[growls]
Hmmm.
[NARRATOR] The intensity
of the first match
between Yamcha and
Tien is about to heat up.
What is Yamcha's new technique,
Wolf-Fang Blowing Wind?
And will it be enough
to protect him
against Tien's own
awesome power?
Find out next time as
the Quarter-Finals continue
on Dragon Ball!