[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball,
Goku and Krillin
continued their training
under the watchful eye
of Master Roshi...
[NARRATOR] A new day dawns
on this tranquil island...
A new day, full
of new challenges...
[NARRATOR] Now, before the
morning dew has left the ground,
Goku and Krillin resume their
rigorous training schedule...
With an added fifty
pounds of turtle shell
strapped to their backs!
[NARRATOR] Each day, Master
Roshi keeps the boys sweating
by boosting their
workload even more!
The fields they
run get longer...
[NARRATOR] The mountains they
climb get taller and taller...
[NARRATOR] And yet, the two
half-pint warriors endure...
Because the World Martial Arts
Tournament is fast approaching,
and these boys are determined
to fight...! At any cost!
[GOKU] Krillin,
I was wondering...
[KRILLIN] Oh yeah?
[GOKU] Yeah...
[KRILLIN] What... about?
[GOKU] Why...
...does that big mean
dinosaur chase us
everywhere we go?
[NARRATOR] And so,
months on the island passed
with relative calmness...
And the strength
of the boys increased...
[NARRATOR] Fortunately,
so did their speed...
[NARRATOR] Before long,
it seems Goku and Krillin
will complete
their basic training
and be ready to learn
Master Roshi's martial arts!
[KRILLIN] Almost...
[GOKU] Yeah...
Darn... That means
I'll have to work!
[GOKU and KRILLIN] More please!
[LAUNCH] Uh, okay...
[LAUNCH] Yes, of course!
[GOKU and KRILLIN] More please!
[LAUNCH] Oh my!
You boys gobbled it all up!
But don't you worry!
[LAUNCH] There's more
where that came from!
Something wrong, Master?
You stuck?
I betcha' can't eat all this!
[LAUNCH] Watch your fingers!
[ROSHI] Here we go!
[LAUNCH] Roshi??
[KRILLIN] Now he's really stuck!
[GOKU] Wait don't move
I need some rice!
[NARRATOR] On and on
the training days passed...
until the Tournament
was only one month away.
[GOKU] Master Roshi!!
Come on...! Hey...!
It's an emergency!
Uh...? What kind?
No time to talk!
Just come with me!
Hey! Can't we take it easy?!
[GOKU] This is it! Look!
[ROSHI] Yeah, it's a rock...
What's your point?
You said if we moved
it you'd teach us fighting!
You remember?
I... said that?
See!
I moved it too...!
Almost as much as Goku did!
There...!
You get to teach us
about fighting now!
Oh... yes... How nice...
[ROSHI] That rock thing was just
a joke to keep them working...
Guess I should have
pointed to a mountain...
[KRILLIN] Real Martial Arts!
Finally!
[ROSHI] Uh, Well boys...
I have almost nothing
left to teach you about...
...the Martial Arts.
[GOKU] What??
[KRILLIN] Master?!
The whole secret behind
the Turtle Hermit fighting style
is the training schedule...
...which you've done every day!
You boys don't
seem to realize
but just by repeating
these basic exercises
over and over again,
you've pushed your arms
and legs and hearts
and even your brains past
their built-in limitations!
That right there is the
whole art behind Martial Arts!
But how are we s'posed
to win if we can't fight?
Well...
You boys didn't come here
to win... you came to learn.
But don't sweat it!
You know how to fight!
It's just the outer
expression of your strength!
It's natural!
Uh, but aren't there special
moves, or tricks to win?
What, is there an
echo in here Krillin?
I just said winning
wasn't the real point!
This tournament is only
another step in your training!
It's an introduction!
And that's the low-down.
There's no point teaching
you special moves
until you get the
fighting experience,
so keep training the same.
But...
...we're going to make
it a little harder...
Now you'll be wearing
heavier turtle shells...
They're twice the weight!
[KRILLIN] So what
do you think, Goku?
You think there's
even a chance
we won't get creamed
at the Tournament?
Who knows?
Maybe all we have to do
is pretend our opponents
are like another day
of construction work.
[wolf howls]
[YAMCHA] Wolf Fang Fist!
[YAMCHA] It's been
over a month now...
...and yeah I'm... strong...
But it's too quiet...
Perhaps I should return.
[BULMA]
I have just about had it!
[PUAR] Oh Bulma,
please don't say that!
Why... not?!
Because it's always
been Yamcha's dream
to fight in the Tournament...
and it doesn't mean
he stopped liking you!
Four whole weeks and
he doesn't even call!!
He didn't send
me a letter or flowers
or even a stinking postcard!!!
Face it baby...
By now... he's
forgotten your name...
Well I would
not be surprised!
You saved me!
Who are you?!
Hm? Come on...!
It's me...! Look!
What...? Me who?
Yamcha!!
[PUAR] Yay!!
Hello Puar!
I missed you!
How's it been here?
Oh... Like a beach
without sunshine!
Oh fine!
You ignored me
all month long!
Why wouldn't you ignore me now?
Uh... I...
[BULMA] Yamcha...
I was worried about you!
For all I knew you
were dead in a ditch
in a country you
can't pronounce!
You'll have to
make this up to me...
And you're
going to enjoy it!
[BULMA] Now let's
go clean you up!
[YAMCHA] O-kay...
[NARRATOR] And so the
last month counted down,
until the Tournament
was only one day away!
Okay boys...!
Did you remember to
pack your toothbrushes?
[KRILLIN] Yes sir!
[GOKU] Tooth what?
Okay... You can take
off your shells now.
Oh good...!
I was scared we'd look
silly at the Tournament!
My body's so light now...!
I feel like paper!
[ROSHI] See how
high you can jump.
Hey Goku...
Notice something different?
[GOKU] Wow! Look how
fast we can run!!
[KRILLIN] We're unstoppable!!
Hey boys, I've got
something for you!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Well...
Since you're going to your
first big tournament...
[LAUNCH] I thought you
should wear something nice!
Launch did you
make these yourself?
I've never worn
one of these before!
Oh...! You look... adorable!!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
What's so funny?
You in a suit.
Hey...
Let's get this baby moving
or we're gonna miss our plane!
Do your best!
Thanks!
See you soon!
Hahaha!
Enjoy yourself Launch...!
And try not to sneeze!
[LAUNCH] Bon Voyage, boys!
Oh wow...! It's like
a flying house...!
What do they call
this thing again?
Airplane.
[GOKU] How neat...
Would anybody care for
some coffee or orange juice?
Can I help you sir?
[mumbling] Eh...
no... I'm fine...
Oh, no...!
Look Master...!
There's stars on the ground!
[ROSHI] Oh, don't worry!
Those are city lights!
We've arrived!
Wow...! So they
make stars in the city?!
You think they'll
give me one, Master?
Caveman...
It's so big...!
Oooh...! And bright!
Why don't we play
the quiet game...
You start.
Hey, Taxi!
Can you take us
to the Colliseum?
[TAXI DRIVER] Yeah, sure...
[ROSHI] Thanks for the ride!
[BULLHORN GUY] Anyone who
hasn't registered please come
to the front tables at once!
You have until midnight!
[GOKU] Gosh!
The world's just full
of people... isn't it?
[ROSHI] This where we sign up?
Yes... Just need your name.
No... it's not me...
It's those two.
[RECEPTIONIST 1]
Oh, you mean you want seats!
No, no...
They're entering the Tournament!
Uh? You mean
those kids there?!
[ROSHI] Naturally!
Do you see any others?
[YAMCHA] Hey...! Hey Goku!
[YAMCHA] Goku!
Did you say my name?
[YAMCHA] Hey Goku!
How's it going?
[GOKU] Who's... He?
Ha...! Wolf Fang Fist!
Yamcha!!!
I thought you'd like that...
Oh...! Wow...!
I guess I didn't recognize you
because your hair
fell off your head!
Bulma said long
hair is out this year...
Who's the tall guy?
[GOKU] He's Yamcha...!
He's friends with me!
This guy's named Krillin
and he's my new friend
and training partner!
Krillin...
Hello!
Well... It's done...!
You're signed up!
Huh? Goku??
Bulma...! Oolong...! Puar!
And lookin' sharp!
You think so?!
So how've you guys been?
Great!
Goku...!
How in the world did you
wind up at the Tournament?
[ROSHI] Hello!
Oh gosh it's you...!
Hey thanks for telling me
that you were moving...!
I stopped by the island
to see how Goku was doing
and your whole house was gone!
Well... that pad
is more for loving
than training Martial Arts...
Bulma...
I keep thinking 'bout
the last time I saw you...
Remember?
You wore that bunny suit...
Remember...? Remember?!
Why don't you
put it on and we--
Shut up!!!
Old Man... Filthy as dirt.
Well Goku, I guess tonight we
better hang out together
while we still can!
Because we're
all gonna be rivals
at the Tournament tomorrow!
[GOKU] Hold on...
I thought the
Tournament started tonight!
Afraid not, kid...
Everyone gets checked in tonight
but it all starts
in the morning!
Oh man... But I want to start!
[NARRATOR] Happy as they were
to be reunited with old friends,
the time for
catching up was short.
Goku and the others needed
to get plenty of rest
for the big day,
when the curtain for the
World Martial Arts Tournament
would at last be drawn.
Oh, I hate crowds...
Do you think
they're all fighting?
Well... Punch one and... see...
Okay... Just stay
close to me boys...
Don't get lost staring...
[BULLHORN GUY] Would all the
athletes who are registered
for the World Martial
Arts Tournament
please gather in
the Contest Hall?
Loud-mouth...
Now are you absolutely
sure you want to enter?
Oh of course!
We're gonna win it!
We promise we'll be good!
[ROSHI] This is as far
as I can escort you...
So do your best!
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Right!
Now one... More thing...
You obviously can't
fight in suits, so... Here!
Wow...! This outfit's awesome!
It's so bright...!
I hope we don't stand out...
Looks good Goku...!
Yeah!
The first roadblock will
be the elimination round,
and only eight top fighters
from there will move
to the actual Tournament,
so take it seriously...
I'll be watching
from the crowd,
so you won't see me, okay...?
We'll work hard Master!
Put your gut into it!
Yeah...
I've been training
way too hard not to...!
And I'll try not to get hurt!
[GOKU] Wow... so all
these people can fight?
I'm starting...
to feel a little queezy...
Attention...! The World
Martial Arts Tournament
Elimination Round begins!
[NARRATOR] Finally, months
of intense preparation
will be put to the test...!
Will Goku and
Krillin's training get
them through the narrow
elimination round...?
And what about Yamcha...?
You have to watch to find out!
Next time, on Dragon Ball!