[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball:
Goku has a promise to keep,
and that means battling
his way up Muscle Tower
to save the
kidnapped village chief.
On the journey upstairs,
he encountered
the menacing Murasaki,
who brought in some
outside help to shift the odds
of winning the fight
in his favor.
We are the five
Murasaki brothers!
Now wait a minute!
Let's talk about this, okay?
[NARRATOR] But try as they
might, the five purple ninjas
were no match for Goku
and his power pole.
Boy, you sure like to run a lot.
[NARRATOR] Murasaki
retreated to higher ground,
where he could
call on reinforcements.
Now, Goku will have to face
the Red Ribbon Army's
most fearsome creation:
the monster, Android Number 8!
Wake up! It's your turn!
Destroy the boy!
Caught you!
[thunder rolling]
[thunder crashing]
[laughing menacingly]
Hey, Number 8,
you want to come out and play?
[MURASAKI] How about
a game of kick his can...
...to the street!
[thunder crashing]
Uh-oh, he's giant!
[MURASAKI laughing]
Yes, he's massive...
And as mean as he is big!
Come on now, let's show him
how wicked and
terrible you can be.
What about these?
Huh? Oh, wait, the key...
Hang on, I know it's in here.
No need.
[MURASAKI laughing]
Did I mention
he was strong, too?
[neck cracking]
Ah, that feels better.
All right! Now get started!
Take care of this nuisance.
[NUMBER 8] I'd rather not.
Huh?
What was that?
You... no, no!
Surely you do not defy me.
Yes, excuse me,
but I hate violence.
Hey, I don't remember
asking for your opinion.
Your job is to spread
mayhem, not philosophy!
Well, I just think that what
you are doing here is wrong.
I mean, especially
how you're holding
the village elder
hostage upstairs.
I've had enough of your mutiny!
Don't you know the
Red Ribbon Army created you?
How dare you refuse
to obey your makers!
I'm sorry... I can't do it.
[MURASAKI] Wh-What?!
You're nothing but a
yellow-bellied coward!
Call me what you want.
I still can't.
Well, now it has
come to this, Android 8.
Do you see this remote?
We planned for an
incidence just like this.
A surprise was implanted in
your body when you were built.
Let's call it
obedience insurance.
All I have to do is
press this big red button
one time and then...
...Boom!
The bomb inside you goes off!
[MURASAKI] So if you don't
want to be blown to smithereens,
you will shut your trap
and follow my orders!
I can't, no matter
what happens, do harm.
You... Y-You ingrate!
[WHITE] Thankless hunk of metal!
What a disgrace!
A technological failure!
[WHITE] Murasaki!
I want you to destroy that
miserable traitor immediately!
Yes, General White!
Hey! Back off, you fool!
[MURASAKI] You asked for it.
Prepare for your last blast!
[GOKU] No! Don't!
Well, then, bombs away!
Don't you dare!
Ready...
[MURASAKI] Set...
[GOKU] Stop it!
[GOKU] I won't let you!
My controller! You destroyed it!
And you're next!
[MURASAKI yelling]
[GOKU] Ha! It serves him right!
No... Another defeat...
Can't anyone stop him?
[GOKU humming]
Thank you
for helping me, friend.
No problem, but you
coulda knocked him out
by yourself, you know.
No. That's mean.
But wait, they are
the bad guys, aren't they?
Wasn't it mean of
them to try to blow you up?
I... I'm just...
...scared.
Oh. But you look so strong.
What's your name?
Goku. How about you, mister?
Oh. My name?
They call me Android Number 8.
That's a funny name.
How'd ya get that?
Just the weirdest name...
Yep. The weirdest one
I've ever heard.
Goku...
Don't you want
to find the old man?
Oh! I almost forgot!
[GOKU]
I guess I'd better get moving.
Bye! Good luck!
Attention all soldiers!
All soldiers!
[WHITE] The enemy has overcome
the third floor guards
and is now making his way
through floor number four.
Be on alert for combat orders.
Hey, what is this?
[GOKU]
What're all these walls for?
[GOKU] Wait, this is a dead end!
[GOKU]
This isn't the way out, either.
Wha--?!
What kind of a
crazy room is this?
[yelling]
[GOKU]
What was that?
[GOKU] I'm just running
around in circles!
[yelling]
[GOKU]
Whoa!
I can't believe I'm
right back where I started!
[WHITE] He's exhausted
himself in the labyrinth.
He can't beat
my impossible maze.
[laughing menacingly]
Huh?
[WHITE] Where do you
think you're going?
[GOKU] Not again!
[distant heavy footsteps]
[heavy footsteps]
[heavy footsteps continue]
Need some help, Goku?
Hey! You're here. How come?
It seems that you are having
trouble finding the stairs.
I will guide you to them.
You know the way upstairs?
I saw the floor plan
a long time ago.
Follow me.
Thanks a lot!
I owe you one!
But you've already helped me.
I'll bet I
coulda looked for hours
and still not
found my way out of here.
I know.
It does seem hopeless.
No, it's this way.
[GOKU] Oh, right.
Hey, Eighter,
is this the fifth floor?
No. We are between
the fourth and fifth levels.
Oh!
Hey, why did you
call me that name, "Eighter"?
Oh, that's just a nickname.
"Android Number 8"
is sort of a lot to say.
Ah, Eighter.
Eighter... Eighter.
I like!
Eighter... Eighter...
He's kind of weird.
So... how's that?
[FATHER] Okay.
There's nothing to worry about.
How long must this go on?
Well, until they
find the Dragon Ball.
I-I hate to think about it,
but when the ball
is finally recovered,
what'll they do to our village?
[GOKU] Okay!
I'll go get your chief now!
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] Don't worry about me!
I'll be fine!
--Oh!
--What's up, Eighter?
I hear...
What is it?
Soldiers... many soldiers.
[yelling]
Oh!
Are you all right? I'm sorry.
Hi there!
There's the menace!
Hyah!
What is it?
Freeze, scoundrel!
Are you okay, Goku?
I'm here!
I think we should go this way!
[GOKU] Oh!
Not again with the dead-ends!
That's impossible...
There was no wall before.
I'm sure of it.
Let's find another way.
[chuckling evilly]
There's nowhere to run, cowards!
[NUMBER 8] What?
What's the matter?
Quickly! We should
run back to that hall.
The last hall.
The fools...
When will they give up?
[GOKU]
There's no use! We're trapped!
[GOKU] Hey! Eighter!
No, wait!
I knew it!
Stop it!
Hey! We did it!
Hurry!
We beat it!
Yes, we did.
[laughing]
[NUMBER 8] The fifth level is
on the other side of that wall.
[GOKU] Huh?
But... But where's the door?
There are only bricks here.
[NUMBER 8] There's no
door into the fifth floor.
A secret room is back there.
But I don't know anything
about what's inside.
Oh...
[NUMBER 8] This is the
sixth floor command room.
The old villager is being
held hostage in here.
A-ha!
Hey! You there!
Are you the one in charge?
Hand over the village chief now!
I'm surprised you made it.
I'm impressed.
You're a fierce rival.
I would like
you to join my army.
Blegh! Blegh!
No way!
This is a horrible place.
General White, sir.
Please put an end
to your evil ways.
Ah... The dirty
traitor speaks out.
Well, you still have a tongue,
but your guts are gone.
[growling]
That's not true.
Who brought you to life?
Tell me.
[WHITE] Remind me...
Who was it that built you
painstakingly piece by piece?
Who gave you this body?
Tell me who it was! Tell me!
Sir, it was
you, General White,
and the Red Ribbon Army.
Now is your last chance, Eight.
You can still destroy the kid.
For me. For the army.
I just cannot do it.
I won't be a part
of your bad deeds.
I beg of you.
The boy is very strong.
Please surrender. It's the
only thing that you can do.
I've had it with this guy!
It's time to stop being nice!
I think it is you who
should be surrendering.
--Huh?
[yelling]
[chuckling]
[GOKU and NUMBER 8 yelling]
[NARRATOR] Uh-oh!
Just as Goku finally managed
reach the top of Muscle Tower,
a tricky trap door has
sent him and his new pal,
Android Number 8,
on their way down again.
But what kind of trouble has
our hero fallen into this time?
Goku and Number 8 confront
the horrors of floor number 5
on the next heart-pounding
episode of Dragon Ball!