[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
While celebrating
Tien Shinhan's victory
over the Martial
Arts Tournament,
cheer gave way to despair as
Goku was gripped with fear
over the absence of Krillin,
who had left the party
to retrieve Goku's four-star
Dragon Ball and Power Pole.
[NARRATOR]
Unfortunately,
Krillin's promise of a quick
return was never realized.
Overcome with dread,
Goku raced in search
of his missing friend.
What he found was unimaginable.
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU]
No, Krillin, I'm here. Wake up!
Krillin!
He's gone...
[NARRATOR]
And now, our story continues.
[panting]
Hm?
Huh?
What happened, Goku?
Oh, no!
Impossible!
Poor Krillin...
He's dead.
[gasps]
It can't be true. It can't!
[ALL gasp]
Easy.
[ANNOUNCER] It was a monster.
A hideous monster!
It took a strange ball
covered with stars
and a list of the
Martial Arts Society.
A Dragon Ball and names?!
A monster.
[ANNOUNCER]
Krillin...
He tried to stop the beast,
but it was too strong.
That boy fought with
everything he had.
[GOKU sobbing]
Krillin, he's gone.
He didn't deserve this!
Bulma, do you have
the Dragon Radar?!
Yes.
Goku, wait!
Come back here!
Stop!
That's an order!
[YAMCHA]
Goku!
There are two near
here. Which one?
Have to guess!
And hope I choose the right one!
[TURTLE panting]
Tha-That's it. From now on,
this turtle's taking a taxi!
Goku.
Impetuous!
That thing was strong
enough to kill Krillin.
And Goku running off
right after a big match--
He won't have the
energy to defeat it!
He was a brave soldier.
Not fair.
Who could be so cruel?
I found this piece of
paper lying on the ground.
Do you think it has
anything to do with it?
It's the word Devil, circled.
Devil? That sounds creepy.
[ROSHI gasps]
Let me see!
[ROSHI] No! It's impossible.
It can't be true!
What's the matter?
Master, what does that mean?
[grunts] Master Roshi?
This is... This is the
crest of King Piccolo.
King Piccolo?
Piccolo? Someone actually
admits to having that name?
I've heard that name.
It's a legendary creature
that is said to have
thrown the world
into the depths
of terror ages ago.
It's true.
[ROSHI] His name may sound
funny, but I can assure you...
There's nothing humorous
about that savage beast!
With him came
darkness and chaos.
His minions of terror
wreaked havoc upon the land,
destroying all in their path
with indiscriminate fury.
[roars]
[whimpers]
[MONSTER growls]
[laughs]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[MONSTER cackles]
[SOLDIER]
Fire!
[roars]
[screams]
[MONSTERS cackle]
[whimpering]
[ROSHI] No one knew what they
wanted or why they had come.
But they were here, laughing as
our world crumbled around them.
Piccolo and his army destroyed
one city after another
with little opposition,
except for one temple.
It was in this
secluded sanctuary
the beasts faced a meager
but determined school
of martial artists.
[ROSHI]
As the horde invaded the temple,
the young fighters banded
together for a final assault.
Though hopelessly outnumbered,
they were united.
And with their
combined strength,
they offered a
formidable defense.
[ROSHI] Many demons fell
that day, and alongside them,
even more great men.
When the battle was over,
only two of the warriors
were left standing.
[ROSHI]
Myself and Crane Hermit.
Unfortunately, the skirmish
had barely made a dent
in Piccolo's forces.
[ROSHI]
Desperate and out of time,
we concentrated our
remaining energy into a shield
that absorbed the
enemy fire and,
with a breath of luck,
reflected it back at them.
[ROSHI] One bright light...
That's all I remember.
But somehow, it worked.
The horde was vanquished.
It was finally over
or so we thought.
[ROSHI] Apparently, the monsters
were just an opening act
for King Piccolo himself.
We barely got a
glimpse of his ugly mug
before he dismissed us
with a wave of his hand.
Against his might, we were but
rag dolls caught in a storm.
Shen and I were
young and in our prime.
We gave everything we had, and
still, King Piccolo prevailed.
All those lives lost and we
didn't lay a scratch on him!
He was immune to
everyone, even Mutaito!
Who's Mutaito?
[ROSHI]
He was my master.
Why have you attacked?
This massacre was
completely senseless!
[PICCOLO] Do you want the truth?
That it was mere amusement.
Or do you need a
higher purpose? Perhaps fate.
[MUTAITO] But we pose no threat.
We are seekers of peace.
[PICCOLO]
And you shall find it in death.
I tried to be nice.
Now we'll do it the hard way.
[PICCOLO]
Foolish.
[gasps]
[groans]
[PICCOLO]
You want more?
[yells]
[groans]
[PICCOLO] Very good.
Where did you learn to dance?
[groaning]
Master Mutaito is
completely under his control!
No, it's not true!
[PICCOLO]
What's so hard about that?
Master, no!
[laughing]
[groans]
[ROSHI] Thanks to
a strong immune system,
and my extraordinary
bedside manner,
Master Mutaito
made a full recovery.
However, exterior wounds
tend to heal much faster
than those we keep inside.
For my master,
the shame of being dishonored
in front of his students
and the loss of the ones
he couldn't protect,
was more than he could bear.
Unwilling to continue
his teaching, he left,
hoping time could mend
what his heart could not.
[GOKU panting]
Never should've happened!
Not to him. Not to Krillin!
You'll pay for this!
Do you hear me?!
You're gonna pay!
[YAMCHA]
It's strange picturing you
and the Crane Hermit as friends.
What you went through,
I had no idea.
[sighs] Neither did I. Crane
Hermit never spoke of his past.
Not to us.
Yeah.
[ROSHI] Something changed
in Shen that day.
I could see it in his eyes.
It was as if goodness
itself had betrayed him.
Whether it was our
Master's leaving
or just the alluring
power of evil, who knows.
He snapped.
The man I knew, my friend,
was gone. Another casualty.
[OOLONG]
Gee, that's too bad.
So what happened next?! How did
you defeat King Piccolo?!
[ROSHI] I didn't. King Piccolo
continued his rampage,
covering the land in
a sea of fire and ash.
Unable to defeat him, I fled.
[OOLONG] You ran?! I would
have stood my ground.
[ROSHI] Obviously, you've
never fought a titan!
If flesh and blood
were as strong as pride,
we would all be invincible.
Fortunately, I found
refuge in the mountains,
where I continued my
training as best I could.
But as the years passed,
I lost hope and began to feel
the weight of my solitude.
Then one day,
that hope returned.
[ROSHI] My mentor had
spent his time away
strengthening his abilities
and in search of a means
to defeat King Piccolo,
which he had finally discovered.
[MUTAITO] Cease fire
and surrender, Piccolo!
Or face the consequences.
[PICCOLO]
0h, I prefer to watch you dance.
Enjoy.
[PICCOLO]
What?!
[yells]
[ROSHI]
The Evil Containment Wave
successfully trapped
King Piccolo.
[MUTAITO]
Open the jar! Now!
[ROSHI] The electronic jar
my master had acquired
was specifically designed
to hold and contain evil.
[MUTAITO]
Quickly, close it! Close it!
[ROSHI] Piccolo's fate was
sealed, but at a heavy price.
Having used up
all of his energy,
Master Mutaito could not endure
the affects of the battle.
He gave his life
to save others,
and in doing so,
regained his honor.
As for Piccolo,
I obeyed my master's
last command
and threw the jar into the sea.
No one has ever seen or heard
from King Piccolo since...
Until today.
Oh no! What if Crane Hermit
found it and opened it again?!
[ROSHI] No. Shen, more than
anyone, understands the danger
of releasing King Piccolo
from his prison.
But, Master, the note and
description of the monster
suggest it could be one
of Piccolo's minions.
[OOLONG, PUAR whimper]
Where did you say
those mountains were?
[ROSHI thinking] If you're
right, Goku's in grave danger.
[GOKU yelps]
There's more than one way
to get across. Flying Nimbus!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
There you are.
Faster, Nimbus.
He's straight ahead of us!
What will we do if the
monsters come back?!
This is horrible.
Even if King Piccolo
is responsible,
there's a chance Goku
won't be able to find him.
Don't bet on it, pal.
That's why he took
Bulma's Dragon Radar.
[ROSHI]
What's he after?
I understand taking
the Dragon Ball.
But why steal a member list
of the Martial Arts Society?
Wait a minute! What's all
this talk about dragons?
Radars, balls! What's that
got to do with anything?
Goku, what are you
getting yourself into?
Seven for one wish.
I like the sound of that.
[cackles]
It is marvelous.
Born leaders, like us,
only need one wish
to rule the world!
[cackles]
I don't need magic
balls to rule this Earth.
It has fallen at
my feet once before.
[SHU]
Then what do you want?
The greatest prize
of all, eternal youth.
Just think. With eternal youth,
I could master time itself!
Why would I wish to rule
this planet for a lifetime
when I could rule
it for all time!
Yes, I agree.
By the way...
there's something I'd
like to run past you.
If you recall,
it was I who plucked
you from the cold sea
and freed you from that jar,
brought you here
to my aerial palace
to recuperate in lavish style.
Did you get those
grapes I sent you?
And I even briefed you on
the Dragon Balls, remember?
Get to the point, Pilaf.
[PILAF, MAI, SHU yelp]
I know you have
a busy schedule.
But, Lord Piccolo,
when the world does fall
under your eternal control...
[PICCOLO]
Yes?
Well, I was wondering
if you wouldn't mind that
I'd keep, say, half of it?
Wait! I, you know, I don't
need that much space.
A third of the world
will do me just fine.
I'm your guy, right?
Who told you about
the tournament?
--[PICCOLO growls]
--[PILAF, MAI, SHU yelp]
Did I say a third?
I meant a quarter.
I'm horrible with fractions!
Anything! A country you don't
want. I know of some swampland!
[PICCOLO]
I'll think about it.
Could you throw in some
furnishings and landscaping
to raise property values?
Pilaf, where's Tambourine?
Uh, Mai!
Yes!
[MAI] Sensors indicate he's
headed this way, sir.
Here he comes.
[PILAF] Wait till you see
a Dragon Ball up close!
They're so nice and shiny!
What I can't figure out
is why you'd want a list
of members of the
Martial Arts Society.
I'm telling you,
those people are dull!
[growls]
[PILAF, MAI, SHU yelp]
Martial artists.
It was one of their ilk
that sealed me in
that cursed jar,
with some trick.
The arrogance!
[growls]
[screaming]
The world's strongest
fighters are on that list.
They will all be destroyed.
All of them.
N-No fighters here.
--In four seconds...
--[ROSHI] That's it!
You don't have to yell!
We're right here!
I figured it out.
I know who killed Krillin
and why they took that list.
Who?!
It was King Piccolo.
Somehow he escaped.
Knowing it was a fighter
who used the Evil
Containment Wave to trap him,
he stole the list
to learn of his enemies.
I get it! With a
phonebook of his enemies,
he can easily track them down.
So he guards
against the wave
by killing those who
know how to use it!
[ROSHI]
Exactly!
[ROSHI thinking]
If there was only some way
to warn Goku before
it's too late.
Aha! Gotcha!
[GOKU]
Now you're gonna pay!
[NARRATOR] Will Goku take
revenge for Krillin's death,
or suffer the same
fate as his friend?
Find out on the next exciting
adventure of Dragon Ball!