[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Piccolo terrified the
citizens of Eastern City
and it was up to
Goku to stop him.
The young hero did his best
to send the monster sailing,
but, even though he made
every punch and kick count,
Piccolo was still able to put
Goku's leg out of commission
with a savage energy blast.
But, with the help of his Power
Pole, the battle continued.
[PICCOLO]
I have you now!
[screams]
[NARRATOR] Once the smoke
cleared, it looked like
there would be only
one warrior left standing.
But it was not to be.
Thanks to Tien, Goku
escaped to the skies
and countered with
a power punch
that knocked the
wind out of Piccolo.
[PICCOLO groaning]
[GOKU]
Aw! Darn it!
I couldn't hit him hard enough
because of my sore leg!
That's too bad! 'Cause
you're gonna pay for that!
[NARRATOR] Goku's attitude
made Piccolo go ballistic
as he pulled out all the stops
in a final attempt to destroy
the young warrior.
[NARRATOR]
The devastation Piccolo caused
left him exhausted, but
exhilarated at the same time.
Had he won the battle, and
obliterated Goku for good?
[PICCOLO] That's more
like it! I destroyed him.
Ha! Try again. I'm still here!
[NARRATOR] The fight concludes
today on Dragon Ball!
[PICCOLO gasping]
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU] What's wrong? You
look surprised to see me.
That attack wasn't nearly
as good as the last one!
Uh?! I don't get it.
That's impossible.
How could you survive that?
I've fought all
over the universe
and I've never met
anyone with the stength
to face me in hand-
to-hand combat!
[laughs]
Well I guess I'm not like other
people because I've got a tail.
Ha, ha, ha. Do you wanna see
just how powerful I really am?
Well just try and
attack me again,
if you've got any
energy left! Ha, ha.
Come on I'm ready!
[PICCOLO sputtering]
--[PICCOLO gasps]
--[GOKU groaning]
[gasps]
[PICCOLO laughing]
Now, look who's in control!
I think you'll agree
I've got the upper hand!
--[PICCOLO chuckling]
--[TIEN groans]
Stop it! Leave him alone!
Ow! That's gotta hurt!
You do as I say
or I'll really put the
squeeze on your friend!
[TIEN gasps]
Don't move!
Take one more step closer,
and I'll give this guy
a headache he's never
gonna forget!
--[PICCOLO laughing]
--[TIEN groans]
Let him go!
Uh. Goku, forget about me!
Just make sure you
destroy this monster! Ah!
--Don't give him any ideas!
--[TIEN groaning]
Ah!
Stop it! Stop it, you monster!
--[YAMCHA gasps]
--[BULMA, LUNCH screaming]
This must be the work of
Piccolo. It has to be!
Eastern City's been
completely wiped out.
I've got a bad
feeling about this!
I hope Goku and Tien are safe.
There's nothing here.
Not exactly a great
spot for a picnic, is it?
Hey, Yamcha?
Don't you think its too
dangerous to rush in headlong?
Maybe we should land
and go in by foot?
Yeah, you're right!
What a rip-off! I come
all this way to watch Goku
fight and there's
no sign of him.
Eh?! Uh. That's one big crater.
This doesn't look good,
and I'm not sticking around
to see if it's safe.
All this way for nothing. Hm...
Goku should have
known better than to try
and stand up to a
guy like Piccolo, anyway.
Hm. Well, I guess the poor
guy'll get what he deserves.
There's nothing
I can do about it!
Huh?!
[YAJIROBE] Wait a minute!
He owes me a dinner!
Goku promised to treat
me to a free meal,
and he still hasn't done it yet!
Hey, hold on.
If I find Goku now,
he might be all beaten up,
then I won't get anything to eat
and my life could be in danger.
Wait a minute.
I forgot Goku drank
the Ultra Divine Water.
He won't be beaten that easily!
If Goku is still alive, I can
get that free meal from him.
That'll be all right
with me! Yeah!
This sure was a big
explosion, that's for sure.
It's gonna be dangerous.
I'm gonna go in alone.
Bulma I want you and Launch to
stay here where it's safe, okay?
Uh! No way, mister! We're all
in this together, remember?
But, this is a much safer
place for you to be right now!
Woah!
[BULMA, YAMCHA screaming]
Uh?
[yelping]
Err! Let him go!
Please... I'll do
whatever you want.
That's a good little boy!
Ha, ha, ha.
[growling]
One move, and it's over!
--[TIEN gasping]
--[PICCOLO chuckles]
That's it, just stay
right where you are!
[PICCOLO] You wouldn't
want to cause an accident!
--[PICCOLO] Watch it!
--[GOKU growling]
[yells]
[gasps]
[yelps]
[GOKU groaning]
[laughs] Too bad!
You won't be able to
use that arm anymore.
Look at you. You're
crying like a baby.
You'll have to learn to
be tougher than that!
If you were more like me, you
could overcome anything,
even pain.
There's no way I'd ever
wanna be anything like you.
Are you so sure?
Tien, forgive me... I can't
let him get away with this!
What?! You fool! Don't you
care about your friend's life?
Of course! And if I
have to collect the
Dragon balls to revive
him, then so be it!
Huh? Ha, ha, ha.
[PICCOLO] Haven't you heard?!
I already killed the Dragon!
What?! That can't be!
That can't be true!
Ha! Why would I lie about that?
Even the Eternal Dragon was
no match against my power!
[growls] No! How
could you do that?!
[chuckles] It is over!
Once I exterminate your friend,
there's nothing anyone
can do about it.
[PICCOLO]
Oh, if you move, he's finished.
If you stay where you are,
you're finished!
Either way, you lose!
[growling]
[groaning]
[laughing] Oh my!
That looked like it hurt!
What are you gonna do? You don't
have a leg to stand on anymore!
Crawl, like the insect you are!
Well, your friend here
is no use to me anymore.
He's served his purpose.
I guess I'll finish him later.
Now it's your turn!
[groaning]
[laughs] You can't do anything
now. You're completely helpless.
This battle will soon be over,
and victory will be mine!
[PICCOLO laughs]
Only a fool would dare
to challenge the ruler
of this dark, new world!
[PICCOLO laughing]
[GOKU grunting]
[yells]
Grr. You're mine!
That's what you think, buddy!
I still have one arm
left that I can use!
What?!
[yells]
[BOTH grunting]
I'm coming at you
with everything I've got!
Good luck! I'll block it!
It's time for your
terror to end! Ahh!
[screams]
[groaning] What? No. Goku?
--[GOKU yelling]
--[PICCOLO sputtering]
[PICCOLO screams]
He did it!
I won!
[laughs] I did it!
[GOKU thinking] Master Roshi!
Krillin! I won your revenge!
[gagging]
[PICCOLO] I don't believe it.
He flew right through me!
How could he defeat
me like that?
So, I underestimated
his strength!
[gasps] He's won,
for now,  but my legacy
on this planet
will survive!
[gagging]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
Good luck, my son. Get
revenge for my demise.
Destroy all of my enemies!
[gagging]
[PICCOLO screams]
[yells]
[BULMA, YAMCHA gasp]
[LAUNCH]
Hm?
[YAMCHA] What could have
caused that explosion?!
Oh, no!
Man, that's what I call a
rough landing. Ow! My head!
Huh?
[SUNO thinking] It sounds
like a bomb went off...
[SUNO sighs]
Oh, Goku...
No, Goku.
[gasps]
[yells]
[YAJIROBE grunting]
[sighs]
Mm. Mm. Uh. Ah?
[YAJIROBE]
Hello!
Hello, Yajirobe! What's up?
[BOTH laughing]
[TIEN chuckles]
Ah. Goku's safe.
[YAMCHA, BULMA] Huh?
Hey, whadda ya
think is going on?
I can't see anything from here.
I still have a bad
feeling about this place.
Are you sure that
we should be here?
Yeah. Of course we should.
I always help my friends
when they're in trouble.
This could get dangerous.
Piccolo's a monster!
You'd better be extra careful!
Uh. Right! Don't worry.
I'll keep my eyes peeled!
[BULMA]
Good luck.
[LUNCH, BULMA gasp]
[BULMA] Hey, wait for
us Yamcha! Uh...
Hey Goku, did you know I was
thinking about going after
Piccolo myself?
You were? Yeah, right!
[laughs]
Hey! What's so
funny about that?
Yeah. That's not nice.
Don't forget, Yajirobe
saved your life.
You should at least show
him some respect.
Yeah, you're right!
Sorry, Yajirobe!
No sweat. Hey why don't
you go get in my car
and we'll go get those
wounds fixed up!
Sure. Thanks a lot! Ah...
You okay?
I'll survive.
Listen, take care of Goku, okay?
I'm going back to Master Roshi's
to tell everyone about
what happened out here.
I'll take care of him. Sure.
[grunts] Get well soon, Goku.
Ah... Tien, what about Master
Roshi? Is it true he's gone?
Yes, it's true. And Chiaotzu.
He's gone as well.
The Eternal Dragon?
[GOKU]
I see...
But Goku, after watching you
fight today, you've inspired me
to train harder
than I ever have!
I can't stand that you're
so much better than me!
[laughs] The next time
we meet at the tournament,
I guarantee I'll
be the champion!
[laughs]
We'll see about that!
[GOKU, TIEN, YAJIROBE laughing]
[groans]
When you get well
come back, okay?
See ya later! I'll be waiting!
Sure.
See ya!
Ah. You're incredible, Goku.
[ALL gasp]
I think I must be going
crazy. Was that Goku?
Yeah, it sure looked like him!
You're kidding?!
[NARRATOR] And so, Goku finally
defeated his rival, Piccolo,
in a series of epic battles.
But now, with the
Eternal Dragon gone,
how will he get the Dragon Balls
that he so desperately needs
to revive his friends,
Master Roshi and Krillin?
The future is uncertain,
but you can bet there are
new challenges on
the horizon for Goku.
So don't miss the next
exciting episode of Dragon Ball!