[DRAGON] Make a wish!
[NARRATOR] Previously on Dragon
Ball, Oolong may have saved the
world from Emperor Pilaf,
but now that Goku has caught
a glimpse of the full moon, he
and the rest of the gang have
an all new danger to face!
[APE GOKU roaring]
[roaring]
He's walking away, you guys!
We better make a break for it!
This whole place
is gonna be rubble if
he doesn't change back!
[roaring]
[yawning]
I was dreaming I was a bee...
and I was about
to sting someone!
[MAI and SHU screaming]
[APE GOKU roaring]
[whimpering]
Don't take my honey,
you mean old bear...
Don't take my honey, please!
Emperor, wake up!
[SHU] Uh, sire!
We've got company!
[PILAF] Huh?
[roaring]
[screaming]
Don't just sit there,
you fools!
Get up there and kill it!
Yes, sir...
[SHU] Take that you monster!
[MAI] Get outta here!
You idiots!
Who taught you how to
scare away monsters anyway?!
Watch!
Oooh! Ahhh! Boo! Boo!
[APE GOKU roaring]
[ALL screaming]
All right, come on,
let's go!
There's no time to lose!
[BULMA] Well, then give me
a hand here, you big lummox!
Uh... What?
Do you mean me?
[BULMA] Who do you think I mean?
Waah!
[SHU] Wait up, Mai!
[PILAF] Hurry, Shu!
[SHU] I am!
[MAI] Come on...
What's wrong with this thing?
Why won't it start?!
Maybe because you're
not yelling loud enough?
Come on! Come on! Go! Go!
I'm doing
my best, Emperor!
She's just being stubborn!
[APE GOKU roaring]
[PILAF screaming]
It's all over!
We're doomed!
I did it!
[SHU] Come on, Mai!
[PILAF] Faster!
[MAI] Here we go!
[ALL laughing]
[ALL screaming]
Oh, Bulma! Are you okay?!
What's the matter, kid?
It's my leg!
[OOLONG] Don't worry,
I'll get you!
Hey, Don Juan!
Can't you see I
need a hand here?
I-I'm sorry,
I just... can't.
[PUAR] Come on, Yamcha.
You can do it!
What are you
waiting for?!
[PUAR] Yamcha! Come on!
[YAMCHA growling]
Oh boy!
[APE GOKU roaring]
[YAMCHA screaming]
[roaring]
I just can't bear to watch
my castle being destroyed
like this! My
insurance premiums
are gonna go
through the roof...
Turn around!
[MAI and SHU] Huh?!
You heard me! Go back!
We're going to beat that big
monkey even if we have to ram
this plane up its nose!
Oh, but, Emperor!
Don't you want
to reconsider, sir?
[PILAF] Where's
the eject button?!
You're getting out!
[MAI] Sorry, sir!
Sorry!
[panting]
I did it!
I... I did it!
I can't... believe...
I... did it
Well, I can...
Thanks for playing my
knight in shining armor...
I can't believe I
actually touched a girl...
And I'm still all right!
Die! Die!
Goku!
Oh no!
So he's a big hairy ape! That's
no reason to shoot him!
Eat lead, you big baboon!
[BULMA whimpering]
[APE GOKU roaring]
[roaring]
[roaring continues]
Why, our puny gun
is totally useless!
Now I just think we
made him really mad!
All right then, it's
time we played our trump card...
Fire the heat-seeking missile!
Right!
[MAI] Easy, big boy...
That's it!
Locked on target...
Firing!
Oh no!
[SHU] Bulls-eye!
[PILAF laughing]
[screaming]
[BULMA gasps]
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
I did it! It worked!
I killed him!
Is... Is Goku dead?
Oh, Goku...
[PILAF] Like I always say: 'The
bigger they are, the harder they
fall'! That'll teach
him not to monkey with me!
Wow, he sure is huge!
and smelly...
More importantly,
why did he have to go and
wreck my castle? Just my luck!
It took me ten years
to build that castle...
and now it's gone! Gone!
[PILAF] I hate you,
you... You overgrown ape!
It's gone!
Gone! Gone! Gone!
[screaming]
It's moving!
[PILAF screaming]
[APE GOKU roaring]
He's alive!
Hurry!
It's coming right for us!
[SHU whimpering]
[PILAF whimpering]
Well at least
my head doesn't hurt...
[YAMCHA panting]
Wow, that was close...
No kidding! Too close!
And it doesn't look
like Goku's finished yet!
[APE GOKU roaring]
I guess we'd better
hide out 'til morning
when the moon goes down...
Uhh, let's go that way!
[YAMCHA] Yeah...
[BULMA] Hey!
Aren't you guys
forgetting something...?
Bulma! Are you okay?!
[YAMCHA grunting]
[YAMCHA] No, it won't budge!
Oh no...
[distant crashing]
[APE GOKU roaring]
[OOLONG screaming]
Here he comes!
Quick!
[grunting]
[roaring]
[OOLONG] Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
[YAMCHA grunting]
Thanks, Yamcha!
[YAMCHA] No problem!
[OOLONG] Come on!
[BULMA screaming]
Bulma!
[BULMA] Goku! Look!
It's me! Put me down!
[BULMA screaming]
[roaring]
[screaming]
I guess it's up
to me now to save her...
Yamcha, didn't you
say that Goku's weak
point is his tail?
Yeah! That's it, Puar!
[YAMCHA] It's time...
For my
Wolf Fang Fist!
Hyaah!
Ha, ha, ha!
[slurping]
[YAMCHA shouting]
Huh?!
[YAMCHA screaming]
[roaring]
[BULMA screaming]
Hold on, Yamcha! We're coming!
[roaring]
[growling]
[ALL] Huh?!
Quick, Puar! Now's our chance!
Turn into a giant pair of
scissors and snip off his tail!
Right!
[APE GOKU roaring]
[BULMA] Catch me!
[growling]
Well he's back to himself!
Uh... Well almost...
[GOKU snoring]
[PILAF] So that little
kid caused all of this?
Why didn't one of
you morons kill him
when you had the chance?
[SHU] You wanted to
let them bake, sire!
[PILAF] Oh yeah...
But this is
still all your fault!
Is that clear?
[MAI and SHU] Yes, sire...
[PILAF] My poor castle!
[hysterical whimpering]
[PILAF wailing]
My castle!
[PILAF sobbing]
[PILAF laughing]
It's not over yet!
[PILAF] Here... and here.
Now, listen
carefully, you two.
My Great-Granddaddy Pilaf
used to say there's no
sense crying over your
losses until you've gotten
your revenge. So, let's
get our revenge and let
the crying begin!
Wow, what a guy!
Yeah, he must've
been quite an inspiration.
[PILAF] All right!
Now let's get
those trouble makers!
[MAI] Yeah!
[SHU] Let's do it!
[MAI and SHU] Huh?!
Hey, Emperor Pilaf!
Where are you going, sire?
Never mind me, you fools!
Just get those pesky kids! And
remember the ageless words of
my dear Great-Granddaddy Pilaf!
[MAI and SHU] Wait up!
[GOKU snoring]
That was quite a
predicament that Goku
managed to
get us into, huh?
Yeah, but if he hadn't
changed into that monster
we would have all been
barbecued in Pilaf's cell!
We'd better not tell
him that he stomped his
grandpa to death... It would
just break his little heart.
Did you guys know a
terrible monster comes out
when the moon is full?
But I'm not
making it up, Bulma!
My Grandpa was trampled to
death by that horrible monster.
Oh... It's just
so hard to believe...
So what's the deal?
Is Goku some kind of alien?
He looks normal enough...
I have a feeling he'll
be quite normal now
that his tail's been cut off.
[BULMA] I sure hope so.
I've got enough friends
with weird hang-ups already!
Not mentioning any
names, of course...
Oh boy, he's waking up!
[GOKU yawning]
Goodness!
Good morning, kid.
Hi!
So, feeling light-hearted
this morning, are we?
Yeah!
[GOKU] My-My clothes are gone!
You don't remember
anything, do you, Goku?
Huh?
How about
sharing some of your
clothes with Goku, Oolong?
Anything but my
undies, made of the
finest cotton in the universe,
and supremely comfortable!
Oolong!
Well, all right then,
he can borrow my pants.
[PUAR snoring]
[OOLONG] Check him out!
Now that's a
definite improvement!
That's style!
Your legs are a lot
shorter than mine are.
Hey! What's with
the wise-crack, huh?!
Uh? W-Wuh--?
Uh, didn't mean to
frighten you there, kid.
You didn't.
I just can't seem to stand up!
That's not too surprising.
You probably just
need to spend a
little time learning
how to balance
without your tail.
Why would I
wanna do that?
Wha--? Oh, no way!
My tail's gone you guys!
[GOKU] Oh, where
could it have gone?
I can't believe it!
It's really gone you guys!
I'm sure it was
there last night!
It's just disappeared!
Vanished! I don't know!
Guess I should wait
for it to come back...
You are one strange,
little kid, Goku.
[GOKU] Where's my...
uh... Power Pole?
Oh, it's that way...
Where the castle used to be.
[GOKU] It's demolished!
I sure hope... my Power Pole's
still out here!
Wah! Ow...
Wah!
What are we gonna do now?
We can't look for the
Dragon Balls for a whole
year, so... I guess we
should just go our
separate ways, huh?
Well, yeah, that seems
like the thing to do.
Hey, it's time to wake up,
my furry, little friend.
[BULMA] Oh well. I guess it's
going to be a whole year before
I can have my wish
granted for a new boyfriend...
[YAMCHA] So, I've got to
spend another year acting like
a lunk-head everytime a
pretty girl comes around...
[YAMCHA] I'll never
get a girlfriend!
[BULMA sighs]
[YAMCHA] Hmm!
--Hm?
--Huh?
[GOKU laughing]
Ugh!
[GOKU] Hey Oolong, I found it!
Is there something
bugging you, Oolong?
Yeah, get a load of
Tweedle-Dum and Tweedle-Dee!
[laughing]
It looks like
they're hearing music...
Boy, that's sure weird...
Ooh!
Uh! Oh no! Did I hurt you,
Bulma? Let me see...
[BULMA] Yeah, a
little, but it's okay...
I feel fine now...
[BULMA] You saved
my life, remember?
Uhm, ahem!
I don't mean to
interrupt you guys, but um...
[YAMCHA laughing]
I think Yamcha and I've
decided that we'd like to
spend a little
more time together...
[YAMCHA laughing]
So, why don't we all
go back to the city?
Pretty cool idea, huh?
That sounds good.
But I think I'm gonna go to
Master Roshi's and
train like my Grandpa did.
I wanna get strong!
But Goku, you're the
strongest kid I know...
Yeah, but when I hit that
castle it didn't even shake!
So if someone else can come
along and tear the whole
thing down, I really
need to go and train!
What are you
talking about, Goku?
You're the one
who destr-mmmph!
We'll miss you, Goku...
And what about you, Oolong?
Well, I dunno.
Do you think I look
like a big city pig?
Are you kidding?
You'll be the talk of the town!
Especially with that
underwear on your head!
You're just jealous 'coz I
got these from the dragon!
[laughing]
Oh well,
I guess I'll go...
You guys need me!
I know!
When a year goes by, let's go
look for the Dragon Balls again!
[BULMA] We don't need the
Dragon Balls anymore, Goku!
[laughter]
[OOLONG spitting]
Despicable!
Hey, how will I ever be
able to find my Grandpa's Dragon
Ball if you're not there
with your radar, Bulma?
Well, I'll tell you what, kid.
How about I just give you this
radar as a going away present,
to remind you of all the good
times that we had together.
Oh wow, thank you.
Well, here goes.
[YAMCHA] I guess this
is goodbye, Goku...
I want you to become just as
strong as Master Roshi, okay?
Okay.
You know I'll never
forget you, Goku.
Aww.
Flying Nimbus!
Hey-hey!
All right, Nimbus, to
Master Roshi's, and step on it!
You go get 'em, kid!
You too, Oolong!
[YAMCHA] Hold on, everyone!
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] Yeah!
[ALL] Buh-bye!
[GOKU] Bye! See ya!
I never thought that life
could be such a neat adventure!
[GOKU laughing]
Go!
[NARRATOR] Soon, Goku's skills
will be put to the test when he
joins Master Roshi and begins
the rigors of Turtle Hermit
Training! But what other
challenges await our young hero?
[NARRATOR] A new day dawns,
and a new adventure begins,
next time on Dragon Ball!