[NARRATOR] Previously on
Dragon Ball, Launch's poisonous
pufferfish made everyone
except Goku sick.
Now, they're feeling better
and ready to commence
their training at dawn.
[snoring]
[blow landing]
The boy kicks harder in his
sleep than he does in training.
[giggling]
[LAUNCH] Goku looks
so peaceful there.
I hope I don't sneeze
in my sleep and wake him.
Good food...
[NARRATOR] The boys better get
good sleep while they can,
because their first full day of
Turtle Hermit training starts
soon, and one thing is
for sure: it will be
filled with hard
work... and danger!
[LAUNCH] Ahh...choo!
[rooster crowing]
[alarm ringing]
I never can get
used to that alarm...
[ROSHI] Krillin! Wake up!
It's time to get started!
Early bird and the worm--
you know the saying!
I don't even think the
worms are awake yet...
[ROSHI] Nice try.
Now stop talking
and start dressing!
I'll go wake up Goku.
[ROSHI] Why should he get to
sleep with Launch while I'm
stuck down there with Krillin?
[ROSHI] If it weren't for those
blasted mood swings of hers...
[ROSHI] Oh, uh, a
little peek couldn't hurt...
[lecherous chuckling]
[ROSHI] Quietly, Roshi...
Oh, so quietly!
[ROSHI] Look at Goku lying
next to Launch, so snug!
If it weren't for her infernal
head cold, I would've...
It's tough to see such
beauty wasted on the young!
Mmm... So
hungry... Mmm...
[ROSHI] Hmm, I wonder what
Launch wears when she sleeps?
[ROSHI] Only one
way to find out!
[ROSHI] Oh no! She must
have sneezed in her sleep!
I don't want to be the one to
interrupt her dream cycle!
That would be a nightmare!
[ROSHI] Goku...
Wake... up...
[ROSHI] Be very quiet...
[GOKU] Good morning,
Master Roshi!
[ROSHI] Shh! Shh!
Master, what's wrong?
[ROSHI] Shh!
Don't wake Launch!
[LAUNCH] Mmm?
[LAUNCH growling]
[ROSHI yelling]
Hi!
What are you doing in
my bed, you pervert?!
I slept here, sir.
We only have two blankets.
[LAUNCH growling]
[LAUNCH] Lame excuse,
you little hedgehog!
Hah!
Launch! What'cha do that for?!
That'll teach you to get under
a blanket while it's in my bed!
[GOKU] Haah!
Yaah!
That's not very nice!
Goku, you really shouldn't
play so rough with girls.
You must learn to be
gentle with the young ladies.
Master Roshi,
I've waited so long.
Can we please start training?
Oh! Train--uh, training,
yes, right, right!
I came to talk to you
about, uh, training!
[nervously chuckling]
[ROSHI] Think fast,
Roshi. Think fast!
Strong wind from the south-west,
barometer high, but falling.
Feels like perfect
weather for training.
Yay!
[ROSHI] Today, we embark
on our study of the
martial arts together.
Before we begin, there is
something very important
you boys should know.
[GOKU and KRILLIN] What?
We do not learn martial
arts to pick fights or to
impress girls who will say: "Oh,
beefcake, you're so strong!
I want you!"
Do you understand
what I am saying?
We must master the art of peace
in addition to the art of war.
We achieve victory
by the arts of war.
Victory is won through strategy.
Strategy is derived
from the arts of peace.
However, if somebody
evil threatens you,
or any other good, innocent
people with unethical force,
it is your duty to defend!
[ROSHI] Do you understand?
Yes!
Uh, can you repeat that?
[KRILLIN and ROSHI] Oh boy...
What I mean is that we
learn how to fight so that
we won't have to. We strive to
maintain peace in the universe.
Oh, I get it now! I
think I can understand that!
Didn't even need pictures...
So, we're ready now for
Turtle Hermit Training?
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Yes!
Are you boys sure that
you're prepared for my
rigorous training schedule?
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Yes, sir!
Fine, then we'll warm
up with a brief run.
Follow me!
[KRILLIN] I heard Master
Roshi's training was tough,
but I haven't even
broken a sweat yet.
[GOKU laughing]
[ROSHI] Now halt.
Good morning!
[ROSHI] I'm Master Roshi.
I believe we spoke yesterday.
Of course. I recognize
your voice from the phone!
This is the delivery
route I usually take. See?
[ROSHI] Alright.
I think I've got it.
That's... a whole lot of milk.
Yeah! I sure hope it's all for
us, 'coz I'm really thirsty!
Ready, boys? You can each
take one of these crates to
deliver across the countryside.
We're delivering milk?
It's a good way to
train our bodies.
Um, does that mean
you're all going on foot?
But sir, I've got a helicopter.
Flying in comfort would hardly
be training, now would it?
But every bottle has to be
delivered by breakfast time.
Don't worry, my friend.
I'll have them moving
like lightning!
Boys! Come grab a crate!
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Yes, sir!
Master Roshi, how can
milk delivery be training?
Just wait and see, kid.
Now, let's take
it easy for today.
[ROSHI] Why don't we skip
the three miles to the
first house on our list?
Three miles?!
[GOKU] Skip?
[ROSHI] Skip, two, three, four.
Skip, two, three, four.
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Skip,
two, three, four.
[ALL] Skip, two, three, four.
[ROSHI] Skip, two, three--
[KRILLIN] How much
further, Master?
[ROSHI] Only two
and a half miles!
[ROSHI] Skip, two, three, four.
Skip, two, three, four.
Skip, two, three, four!
Skip... Skip... Skip...
[ROSHI] Come on, Krillin!
We can't have stragglers!
Good! We're off to a good start!
Now, for the
next two miles...
You mean there's more?!
Of course there is!
[whimpering]
Here, how 'bout we
zigzag between the
trees along this path?
Huh?!
Zigzag? What's that?
[ROSHI] When you're ready, go!
Now zigzag!
[ROSHI] Chant with me boys!
[GOKU and ROSHI] Zig, two, zag,
four! Zig, two, zag, four!
[KRILLIN panting heavily]
[GOKU and ROSHI] Zig, two, zag,
four! Zig, two, zag, four!
[KRILLIN] Hmm...
Zig, two, zag, four!
[KRILLIN] Krillin,
you're a genius!
Zig, two, zag, four!
Zig, two, zag, four...
[chanting continues]
[ROSHI] Krillin?!
I'll start over, sir!
[chuckling]
[GOKU] Here's your
new home, Mr. Bottle.
[panting]
If you don't move your
legs faster, Krillin,
the milk is going to curdle!
[whining]
Krillin! Did I say
that you could rest?!
That's better.
You've earned a break from
running. We're going to climb
a few stairs instead.
[KRILLIN] Finally, I can catch
my breath and take it easy.
[KRILLIN] A few steps?!
I may have been hasty
when I said Master Roshi's
training wasn't so tough...
[GOKU] Why can't I
drink the milk?!
[ROSHI] Ah, there's nothing
more relaxing than the
fresh air of nature.
Hmm?
Well, it looks like even
Goku has his limits.
[GOKU] Master Roshi,
couldn't I go faster
with the Nimbus Cloud?
Would that challenge
your abilities, Goku?
I guess not...
[GOKU] It's just that I'm so
tired of climbing stairs...
Did you know? Ox-King and your
grandfather Gohan used to carry
crates up these mountains
all the time, and not once
did they ever complain to me.
What? My grandfather
delivered milk here? Like me?
I'll meet you at the top,
Master!
Worked like a charm.
Good job!
You're half way there!
H-Half...?
[KRILLIN] I could've sworn I was
at least three half-ways there!
[KRILLIN] Each step
feels like my last!
[GOKU] My grandfather
would never stop...
[KRILLIN] I can't let Goku
humiliate me again...
I gotta make it all the way...
[GOKU] At the top...
[KRILLIN] At last...
Delivered before
breakfast.
Thank you. Would you
like a cup of milk, friends?
I do!
Why did you make my
head ouch like that?
You don't give milk
then take it back!
Oh... No thank you, mister Monk.
Master Roshi, it's been
ages since you've trained.
[ROSHI] Yes, it
has. It's nice to see you again.
Always nice to visit
with old friends.
How is the training of
these young ones going?
It's too early for
me to say, really.
But I think that they
are showing great promise.
Did you hear that?!
"Great promise"!
If they get themselves in gear,
they'll be ready for the
World Martial
Arts Tournament.
Oh, that's only eight
months from today!
The World Martial
Arts Tournament?!
What is that?
Are you saying you
never heard of it?!
[KRILLIN] That's where all the
greatest fighters in the whole
wide world meet up and compete
with each other to determine
who is the absolute best!
The absolute best? That's great!
And they only hold
this tournament once
every five years.
[GOKU] Oh, how exciting!
[KRILLIN] Only eight
finalists can participate
in the tournament. But, hundreds
of contestants show up every
five years to try and make it
past the elimination rounds.
[GOKU] That sounds like fun!
[KRILLIN] I've heard
that the competition's
extremely difficult, and
some battles really heat up!
I wish I could enter...
Well, Master Roshi, will we
really be ready to fight?
Only if you boys
train diligently.
Sounds like quite
an incentive...
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Yaay!
[ROSHI] But...
You will not go in there
with hopes of winning the
tournament the first time
you compete. To do so
would be arrogant. And arrogance
is for fools, not warriors.
So you will enter the tournament
with the sole purpose of
improving your fighting skills.
I can't wait! This
is gonna be so exciting!
And by then we're
gonna be so strong!
Not if they don't finish
delivering the rest
of the milk today...
Respect Master Roshi.
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Yes!
[NARRATOR] While Goku and
Krillin's minds filled with big
dreams of the World Martial Arts
Tournament, a familiar face
far away was also
preparing for the big event.
[VOICE] Haa-chaa!
[grunting]
[screaming]
Next!
[NARRATOR] That man
preparing was Yamcha,
the one-time Desert Bandit.
[BULMA] You can do it, Yamcha!
Knock him out! Take him!
[PUAR] Oh, be careful!
[MAN] Me next!
You think you can take me?
Why won't you stand
still you little coward,
and fight once like
a real man, huh?
Not tough enough, is that it?
That beast is going
to beat Yamcha!
Well, don't blame
the beast, Bulma.
Yamcha did knock out
twenty of his friends!
Oh, Puar, can't
you do anything?!
Don't worry.
My Yamcha can defend himself.
[YAMCHA] Hey there, pal. Do
you wanna see my Wolf Fang Fist?
Your what?
You'll see.
Wolf Fang Fist!
[wolf howling]
[screaming]
[ALL] Yay! Yamcha did it!
I knew Yamcha would win,
just like he'll at the
World Martial Arts Tournament!
But Puar, shouldn't you
be worried about Goku?
He's somewhere training
with Master Roshi!
Yeah, that Goku's
no wet noodle.
He's not as strong as Yamcha!
[YAMCHA] This simply will
not do! The competitors
in the Tournament will be
much tougher than this big oaf.
Goku, please show up!
I've got something
I wanna share with you.
He's such a stud!
[ROSHI] Careful, boys. One
foot in front of the other.
Now, balance. Balance!
[screaming]
[ROSHI] Concentrate!
[ROSHI] And no whining!
Breakfast time
is almost here!
Who cares about breakfast when
you're falling down a pit?
[GOKU] I think I'm
thirstier than he is!
[KRILLIN] Me too...
Hurry boys, step lively,
otherwise this sand is
gonna swallow you whole!
Just... think... of... the...
[KRILLIN] World... Martial...
Arts... Tournament...
[ROSHI] Stand firm, boys.
Don't fall with the water.
[GOKU] All the greatest fighters
in the world will be there!
Not... fall...
in... ri--!
The water!
[screaming]
[growling]
Must go faster, boys, if you
don't want him to eat you alive!
Hurry, hurry!
[ROSHI] Good job, Goku.
You too, Krillin.
You'll deliver milk like
this each day for the
next eight months. That will be
your early morning training.
Now then, let's start
the mid-morning training!
[GOKU] What?
[NARRATOR] As Goku and Krillin
have found, Master Roshi's
training is tough indeed.
And it's just beginning!
But with the World Martial
Arts Tournament in the air,
it just might be worth it!