[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
After surviving his encounters
with the Red Ribbon Army,
Goku braved the
urban wilds of West City
in search of
Bulma's technical expertise.
Now, with the Dragon Radar
once again in working order,
Bulma has decided to
accompany Goku on his quest,
and the two
sail the wide blue skies
towards their
next great adventure!
[BOY] Dad! Look! Do you see
the boy riding the cloud?
[BOY'S FATHER] No! But I see one
that looks like an alligator!
[yawns]
We made it to the ocean, Bulma.
Huh?
Okay. Just keep going straight.
[yawns] How much longer?
Well, at the rate we're going
I'd say... forever!
That long, huh?
Yeah. It's too bad the
Flying Nimbus can't go faster.
Huh? Hey! Nimbus! Faster!
[BULMA yells]
G-G-G-G-G-G-okuuuuu!
Fun, huh?
Yeah, Nimbus! Faster!
[BULMA screams]
G-G-G-oku!
Isn't this dangerous?!
Nah! We'll be fine. Watch this!
[BULMA screams]
--[GOKU laughs]
--[BULMA] Goku!
[NARRATOR] With two Dragon
Balls in their possession,
Goku and Bulma are
heading for their third!
But as they'll soon find out,
their innocent search
is leading them straight into
the heart of
the most extreme danger!
[CAT exhales]
[RED]
I wonder if that kid even knows
what he's getting himself into?
[STAFF OFFICER]
I seriously doubt it!
That island base is top secret!
He is most likely
just following his radar.
Aye! Look how fast he's going!
Darn kid! I want him dead!
[CAT hisses]
[RED groans, yells]
Ah! Have you sent out an image
of the boy like I told you?
Yes sir!
Good! Blue will be
ready for 'im!
I don't want that boy
leaving the island alive;
do you understand?!
Right!
[RED] This time the element
of surprise is on our side!
[laughs]
[BLUE] Hmmm. Perfect!
[chuckles]
[knock, knock]
[TIGER] General Blue, sir!
A communiqué has arrived
from our submarine!
I'll be right there! Stay put!
[chuckles]
[BLUE]
So they haven't found it yet?
That's the big news?
[TIGER]
I-I'm afraid so, sir!
[BLUE] You people are lame!
Do I have to do
everything for you?
But, sir!
Our Dragon Radar stinks!
It's true! It only
gives us the general idea
the balls are in!
It's just too vague, sir!
I'm tired of excuses!
That's why you can't find it!
Huh?
You're too busy
picking your noses!
What?
Please, sir! I-I wasn't!
Fool! You're holding
the evidence!
Take him away! Execute him!
What?! No! No...!
[TIGER] Move along, private!
[PRIVATE 1]
But I won't do it again!
[commotion]
[chuckles] Yes...
You! Hop to!
Delouse that station!
Yes, sir!
Sir! A message!
It's in code, direct from HQ!
Headquarters?
Yes, General!
That kid is on his way here!
What? The boy? Coming here?
Well, this should be fun!
But General!
He destroyed the White Corps
and the Silver Corps
single handedly, sir! Aye!
But not Blue, right?
Ahh! Of course not, sir! No!
[GATOR stammers]
Silver and White lost
the fight, didn't they?
[chuckles]
[BLUE] But now we'll see
what Blue can do!
[laughs]
Oh, wow! It's getting
steamy out here!
We're almost there, kid!
Gosh, I can't wait!
My chest is getting sweaty!
Huh?
[GOKU]
Look, Bulma! Underwater birds!
[BULMA]
Those are giant rays, silly!
[GOKU] Wow!
Yo! Hey!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Hi!
--[GOKU] Aah!
--[BULMA gasps]
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Whoa!
Bye!
Yeah! [laughs]
[BULMA] Huh? Goku, wait! Stop!
We made it!
The ball's right below us!
Huh? Really?
[GOKU] But there's nothing
down there except water!
Look, Bulma!
[BULMA]
It must be on the bottom!
I'll bet it's
pretty deep down there!
Yeah, we're gonna
need a home base!
Let's see.
Uh... There!
[BULMA] That island will do!
[GOKU] Right!
Check it out.
There's a boat! Hmh.
[BULMA]
Look out world! I'm coming up!
Whoa.
[groans] Man! What a relief!
Hey! I'll just go get the
Dragon Ball and be right back!
[laughs]
Oh! You want little
ol' me to stay here!
Right? Is that it?
Yeah.
[BULMA] Well forget it, kiddo!
I'm coming, too!
See! I've got Dyno-caps!
Yep! Can't beat 'em!
Now! Instant submarine!
[BULMA yells]
What's wrong?
This! All my capsules
are gone except this one!
Oh, no!
[shrieks]
This is Dad's. We must have
gotten ours mixed up.
Well, maybe there's one of those
"instant subma-thingies"
in there.
[grunts] I wish!
But I seriously doubt it!
Goku! I have a
bad feeling about this!
But there might be something
in there that can help us!
I doubt it!
Well, maybe...
It's possible, I guess.
There could be--
Oh, all right! Here it goes!
Aah!
[GOKU] Gosh, how sad!
These girls must be poor.
They can't afford clothes.
Those girls are not poor, kid!
[GOKU] They're not?
No, sir! Now give me that!
--[BULMA grunts]
--[GOKU] Uh...
[BULMA] Isn't there
a man on this whole planet
with a shred of decency?
Men are animals!
[yelling]
Bulma?
[breathing heavily]
What?
I'm going to go get
that Dragon Ball, okay?
Be right back!
Fine! Whatever!
Bye, Bulma!
[BULMA] Ugh! My own father!
[GOKU] I think this is the
place! It seems about right!
[BULMA sighs]
What am I supposed
to do while he's gone?
This is boring!
Hey, wait!
[BULMA laughs]
If there was a boat,
there must be people!
And where there's people,
there's shopping!
[groans]
[breathes heavily]
[GOKU]
Hey! Bulma! It's too deep!
I can't hold
my breath that long!
Hey, Bulma.
The water's too... deep?
[GOKU] Where'd she go?
She was just here!
If there's a resort here,
they might even have a store
that sells the DynoCaps I need.
Goku's strong, but I don't think
he realizes how deep it is.
Wow! What pretty flowers!
Huh?
[screams, whimpers]
[yawns]
[whimpers]
[sighs] Thank goodness!
Uhhh... I'm starting to think
this island is deserted!
[BULMA] Those scuba divers
must have come from
a yacht or something.
It feels so empty.
[birds cawing]
Huh? No, wait!
[BULMA] There's someone here!
Hey! Hello!
Hi!
Huh?
What?
This can't be happening!
There must be
some mistake! Aaah!
[BULMA]
Help me! Somebody, please!
Why me? This isn't fair!
[BULMA] Help me!
I'm too young to die!
[PILOT 2] Stop right there!
[BULMA] Oh, no!
[PILOT 1] That's far enough!
Hey! It's a doe!
No little buck around here.
Yeah! Roger that!
[yells]
[PILOT 2]
Don't move! Or we'll shoot!
It's... It's over!
[BULMA whimpers]
Well, what do we have here?
Just a frightened girl!
Sorry about that!
[PILOT 1] We thought
you were someone else!
What? This was all a mistake?!
Jerks! Are you crazy?
What's the big idea?!
I could have been killed!
Hey! Relax, babe!
You shot at me!
Come on!
Cut us a little slack, girl!
We were following orders!
That's right! We're
soldiers! Military studs!
[BULMA] I see.
Well, hey! My name's Bulma!
I'm looking for a place to shop!
Maybe find myself
a submarine on discount!
A submarine?
I like to sight see! You know.
Look at all the reefs.
You can't even
buy capsules here, babe!
This island's deserted!
No way! Well, darn!
How strange!
I wonder whose boat that was?
[BOTH] Hm! [chuckle]
Hello! Bulma! Where are you?
Uhh! Man!
She can never stay put!
[GOKU yells]
Uh. Huh?
Yum!
Thanks! See ya, then.
Hold on!
You're under arrest...
for being too pretty!
No joke! What a crime!
Gosh! You men
think I'm pretty, huh?
Uh, huh!
Yeah! Very pretty!
Wow! You soldiers
made my day! Thank you!
We did, aye?
Hhhnnnh!
Mmm!
Hey! Chicky baby!
Let's have some fun, 'kay?
Fun? With you?
[BOTH chuckle]
Hey! Easy does it there, boys.
What do you mean by "fun"?
Fun!
The good kind of fun,
or the bad kind?
Good!
Like swimming?
And hiking? That kind?
[BOTH] No!
[BULMA]
Oh! I see... That fun!
[BOTH chuckle]
Too bad, guys!
I'm only sixteen!
Sorry! No fun!
[BULMA] I'm under age!
[PILOT 2] Yeah, heh-heh.
Can you guys wait?
[PILOT 1 and 2 chuckle]
Yeah!
Sure, we'll wait!
[PILOT 1 and 2 grunt]
[BULMA shrieks]
[BOTH] Time's up! [laughing]
[screams]
[BOTH laugh]
[PILOT 1 and 2 coughing]
[BULMA screams]
[PILOT 1 and 2 grunt, groan]
[BOTH yell, groan]
[BULMA] Take that, ugly butts!
That girl's dead!
[BULMA panting]
Go, Bulma! Don't you stop!
[PILOT 1]
Stop! Or we'll open fire!
[yelling]
Oh, no! Goku, help me, please!
[panting]
Help!
[BULMA] Goku! Where are you?!
[sighs]
That was yummy!
[BULMA] Goku!
Uh, oh! That was Bulma!
[BULMA] Goku! Where are you?!
Oh! Hey! There she is!
[BULMA screams]
Somebody, please!
She's in a bad mood!
Oh, boy! Great!
[GOKU] Coming, Bulma!
[BULMA screaming]
[BOTH chuckle]
[yells. panting]
[laughing]
Hey! What the heck?!
It's about time!
Hey, what's the deal?
Are those guys bad or what?
Yes! Get them!
The boy...
Yeah! That's him!
Whoa! You're right!
[PILOT 2] He's mine!
Huh?!
[GOKU] Ahh!
[BOTH] Huh?
You bullies!
Only scaredy-cats use guns!
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[PILOT 2 yells]
Yikes!
[GOKU] Power Pole, extend!
[GOKU yells]
[PILOT 1 groans]
Power Pole, retract!
Yeah! Hey... Peace!
[beeping]
[GATOR] What?
General Blue! The jet-copters!
They're gone! Kapoof!
They just ain't
there no more, sir!
So... The kid has arrived!
Well then, let the games begin!
[chuckles]
[GOKU] So, I uh, I guess you
didn't find any Dyno-caps, huh?
No, Goku,
I didn't find any Dyno-caps...
Great observation.
Bulma! Guess what?
I just had an idea!
We can go to Master Roshi's!
He lives around here.
Doesn't he?
Ugh!
[GOKU]
He has all kinds of neat stuff!
I'll bet he even has
one of those subma-thingies!
Ick! That old coot!
[ROSHI sneezing]
Oh boy, oh boy!
Eeeh! Goodness!
There must be
a pretty girl nearby!
[ROSHI] That's the only time
I sneeze like that! Heh-heh!
I'm not going there!
What? Sure you are!
You have to, right?
Hey! I'm sure he'll be
really happy to see us!
[GOKU] Come on, Bulma!
I'll let you ride in my shirt!
[chuckles]
[BULMA] No, Goku!
I'm not going! I refuse!
[GOKU] But what about
the Dragon Balls?
[BULMA] I said no--I mean, yay!
[NARRATOR]
As Goku speeds off with Bulma
toward Master Roshi's,
the dastardly General Blue
awaits his return
with eager anticipation!
Join us next time
on Dragon Ball!