[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku fought Baba's masked
fighter in the final match
to determine the fate
of the seventh Dragon Ball.
Goku held his own as he proved
that one Kamehameha wave
deserves another.
[NARRATOR]
Unfortunately, this adversary
knew Goku's one weakness.
Goku had him beat!
This isn't fair!
It's not Goku's fault
he loses his power
when someone grabs his tail!
[NARRATOR] The real shock
came when Master Roshi
revealed the secret identity
of the mysterious fighter...
Gohan, Goku's
deceased grandfather.
[PUAR] Someone should tell Goku!
No! This can't be happening!
Please don't tell me I'm looking
at some kind of ghost!
Goku's grandfather
is most definitely dead.
That halo above his head
isn't just for decoration.
Somehow he's returned.
Why is he hurting Goku?
I don't think
he came all this way
to harm his grandson.
[UPA] Oh, Goku!
[ROSHI thinking] Goku, you must
find the strength to hold on.
If you give up now,
Gohan's visit will
have been for nothing.
Perfect.
With my new power suit,
I will rule the planet
and crush all who oppose me!
[SHU] Sensors indicate
that this is the location
of the Dragon Ball cluster.
Zoom in on Sector G-12.
Who is that?
It's that same
little brat as before!
[MASK MAN]
Oh, what a shame.
All your power wiped out
with one grasp of your tail.
So he does have a weakness.
Shu, we must inform
the Emperor at once.
Finally, victory
is within my sight!
[PILAF laughs]
Of course his tail
is his weakness.
I mean, look at it!
It doesn't even
go with his outfit!
We are now in
a perfect position
to exact our revenge
on the child
and take all six Dragon Balls
in one fell swoop.
His guard is down
and we have the advantage.
Sooner or later,
that boy was destined
to fall at my feet.
I am Pilaf, the invincible!
Tonight, I sleep
without my nightlight!
Refreshing!
We must seek him out.
He certainly won't
be coming to us,
thanks to my specially designed
Compact Anti-Radar
Dragon Ball Shield Container!
Too bad the rights to
the word "lunch box" were taken,
but again, I prove
that nothing can stop me!
With my spy satellite,
I can count every hair
on that brat's nappy head,
yet I could place this
Dragon Ball right under his nose
and he wouldn't even see it! Ha!
Emperor Pilaf,
when we located the boy,
he appeared to be fighting
in one of Fortuneteller
Baba's tournaments,
presumably to
receive aid in locating
the seventh Dragon Ball.
What if she tells him
where to find us, sire?
If she were a
real fortuneteller,
what's she doing stuck
in the middle of a pond?
Besides, look at the
size of her crystal ball.
She rides on it,
for goodness sake!
She's obviously
compensating for something!
And if for some reason
he gets lucky...
...my Power Suits
will reduce him to dust.
Right. Very well, sire.
Behold my brilliance!
These robotic behemoths
will assure my
ascension to greatness
by laying waste to anyone
foolish enough to oppose me!
Don't just stand there.
Grab a suit and capsulize!
[BOTH] Yes, sire!
Once I have all seven
Dragon Balls in my possession,
the Eternal Dragon will be
under my complete control!
And if that big haired freak
so much as looks at me wrong...
Let's just say his short life
won't be getting any longer.
Mai, did you pack
my favorite sandwiches?
[SHU] Those were for you?
[PILAF] Idiot!
[MASK MAN] Had enough?
Are you ready to surrender?
Be smart.
Give up while you
still have a face.
No... I will never give up...
[MASK MAN] Well, it's
your tail on the line, sonny.
No, no, no, no, no!
I can't watch this anymore!
This is insane!
How could he be so
cruel to his own grandson?
Stop it.
Hello! Roshi!
In case you hadn't noticed,
that's your student out there,
and if you don't
do something to save him,
he's the last
one you'll ever have!
Goku needs help!
I don't think he'll
last much longer.
But guys, we can't interfere.
It's forbidden.
If we do, he'll lose the match.
Right. Our helping Goku
now would ruin everything
that we've sacrificed
to get to this point.
Look at him! He's in pain!
We can't just stand here
and do nothing.
There's no other choice.
Is it... over?
[MASK MAN]
Your friends are loyal.
They care a lot about you.
[MASK MAN] Any one of them
would lay down their life
for you, without question.
Hello.
[BABA]
Could we get on with this?
I'm having my
ball waxed in an hour.
[MASK MAN]
Certainly, my dear Baba.
It's almost over.
The boy and I just have a few
more things to pound out first.
I've got it!
I know how we can help Goku!
We can call for a time-out.
They do it in other
sports all the time.
This way we're not
interfering with his match,
but we can still
let him have a break.
A break?
He's already broken!
Ha ha!
If he rests, he might be
able to get his strength back.
No.
No one is going to help Goku.
It is crucial
he faces his grandfather
without interruption.
This is ridiculous!
Goku doesn't even
know who he's fighting!
That fact will be revealed
in time, I assure you.
You must have patience, Bulma.
How much longer
can Goku hold on?!
[KRILLIN]
You mean how much longer
is his grandfather
gonna hold on?!
Gohan was not a reckless man.
We must have faith
in his judgment.
He won't give Goku any more
than he can handle.
Goku will want to see
this fight through to the end.
But why?
Stop making excuses!
What his grandfather
is doing is cruel!
[PUAR screams]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[GOKU grunts]
What have you done?!
[GOKU screams]
[MASK MAN] That had to hurt...
At least you don't have to worry
about people pulling it anymore.
[GOKU] Ow! My tail!
Haha, I don't believe it!
The darn thing came clean off!
So much for that weakness, huh?
Wow!
Now he can win!
All right!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Easy, Goku!
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU] Ow! It's sore!
[GOKU yelps]
You meanie!
Why did you have to
go and take off my tail?!
That isn't fair
and you know it!
You're better!
Goku!
Beat him, Goku!
There's no weakness
to hold you back.
You won't trick me
like that again!
[MASK MAN] I surrender.
Did I just hear you right?
Did you say you surrender?
[MASK MAN laughing]
Hey, wait...
You're really telling
the truth, aren't you?
[MASK MAN] Of course I am.
I surrender. I am defeated.
Okay...
Did... he... just win?
This is most irregular.
[MASK MAN]
Goku, you have worked hard
and grown strong in
such a short amount of time.
How come you
already know my name?
[MASK MAN] Unfortunately,
you never mastered
your only weakness.
This tail would be
your undoing one day.
I always told you that.
Remember?
Wait a minute! Y-You're my--
[MASK MAN] Oh! Thank goodness.
I was so tired of
wearing this mask...
Did the whiskers give me away?
Is that you, Grandpa?
Yes, it is you!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
That's right.
It's me, my boy. It's me!
I'm so happy
to see you, Grandpa!
I've missed you so much!
Where have you been?
I thought you--
[GOKU sobbing]
There, there now.
Stop your crying.
I looked everywhere
but I couldn't find you!
Goku...
I've never seen him like this.
With all his strength
and accomplishments,
it's easy to forget
he's just a kid.
Goku! He's happy!
Goku, how's your
backside feeling?
Does it still hurt?
[GOKU]
Uh-uh.
I didn't mean to
break your tail, my boy.
I was just
trying to prove a point.
You have to learn
to protect your weaknesses,
like I always told you.
Now are you okay?
I'm all right, Grandpa.
Aside from that,
I must tell you,
I was impressed
by your strength.
I never expected you could
beat me in a match.
Have you been taking
lessons from Master Roshi?
Uh-huh.
Master Roshi, it's an
honor to see you again,
my old friend.
[ROSHI] Likewise.
It's been a long time, Gohan.
I almost didn't recognize you
behind that silly mask.
Oh. Well, forgive my secrecy.
I thought it was necessary.
I was afraid if Goku
knew my true identity,
he would hold back
and not use his full power.
Yes, yes, I understand.
How else could you
have accurately measured
the boy's true growth?
[BULMA] Master Roshi.
What is it?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I thought you told us that
Goku's grandfather was dead.
Did... Did you really
come back to life, Grandpa?
Oh, no, Goku.
I didn't come back to life.
For the sake of not passing out,
I'll pretend
you didn't say that.
I'm talking to a dead man.
[BABA] Close your mouths
and open your minds.
I'll explain everything.
This world is divided
into two halves:
The Living World
and the Other World.
I can travel between both.
This comes in handy when
I'm recruiting new fighters.
If I can't
find one on this side,
I just take a little road trip.
And that's where
she met up with me.
That's correct.
Now that you're here,
does that mean you can
come live with me again?
I'm afraid not.
The rules of inter-world
travel are very specific.
I've only got a one-day pass.
So do you think
that running into Baba
was just a coincidence?
[ROSHI] I don't think so.
Knowing my sister,
she knew full well
that Goku and his friends
were coming today.
[chuckling]
Correct.
That fortune was told long ago.
In fact, it was Gohan
who approached me,
asking if a young boy with
a tail would visit me someday.
But I had no idea
Goku was his grandson.
Thanks!
I don't care
how you did it, Baba.
I'm just grateful that
you brought him back to me.
Of course.
I will always be
indebted you to, Master,
for taking on my
grandson as your pupil.
It is clear to me that,
under your guidance,
he has found a mentor.
Not only in martial arts,
but in life as well.
No, no, no, no.
You give me too much credit.
I only taught him the basics.
His strength is as much a
mystery to me as it is to you.
Thank you, my old friend.
Now I can return to
Other World with peace of mind.
Don't mention it.
Incidentally,
does Goku still
turn into a huge monster?
[ROSHI] Don't worry.
Since I broke the moon,
everything has been
nice and peaceful.
Hey guys,
why are you whispering?
What's the big secret?
Nothing... Nothing at all.
I've got something
to show you, Grandpa.
I think you'll like it a lot!
[GOHAN] Goku?
Be right back!
Here it is!
Your four-star ball.
I've been saving it for you!
Oh, yes.
I picked up that doohickey
a long time ago.
It looks like you've been busy
gathering quite a
collection, young man.
Actually, those balls have made
a big impact on
your grandson's life.
Okay, I'll bite. Tell me more.
[BULMA] Certainly.
They're called Dragon Balls.
There are seven of them.
Very popular.
In fact, tracking them down
is how I first met Goku.
[BULMA] Right from the start,
I could tell there was
something different about him.
[BULMA] Goku was enthralled
by the Dragon Balls
and begged me to take him
along when he found out
I was searching for all seven.
I knew it might mean trouble,
but there's always danger when
you have a big heart like mine.
[BULMA] Throughout our travels,
he managed to make
a lot of friends...
[BULMA]
...some easier than others.
But even those he fought
eventually came around.
[BULMA]
Of course, there were a few
who were completely hopeless.
[BULMA] Not everyone
who searched for the Balls
was as selfless as me.
Some were downright despicable!
[GOKU]
...me-ha!
[BULMA]
But no matter the danger,
and I must say
I'm most proud of this,
we did everything we could
to help out the innocent
and punish the morons.
[BULMA] And that's about it...
At least the good stuff.
[GOHAN] I see. Sounds exciting.
You've been very busy, Grandson.
Good thing you had
this young lady
to help you out
of those tight spots.
[chuckles]
See, you're in good hands.
Goku will bring your
father back, no problem.
Yes, but...
What's wrong? Goku won.
Aren't you happy?
How can I ask Goku
to bring my father back?
What about Gohan?
[laughs]
Don't worry about me.
I love it in Other World.
I wouldn't leave it
for anything.
I've got a lot of friends,
and most of them are brunettes.
Save some for me.
Shut up!
In all these years you
haven't changed one bit,
you old air bag!
All this time
I've been looking
for something
redeeming about Baba,
and I think I just found it.
Ow! You left a mark!
Sad thing is,
that's all I can do.
One of life's little ironies...
It doesn't matter
how old you get,
you'll never be bigger
than your big sister.
Thank you very much, sir.
There's no thanks
necessary, my boy.
I'm just glad my grandson
could help you out.
I hate to break this up,
but my feet are killing me
and I can't rest until
I tell the boy his fortune.
Well, I guess you don't need
me around anymore,
so I'll be taking my leave now.
It's been fun.
Wait! What do you mean?!
You can't leave yet, Grandpa.
Saying goodbye
is never easy, Goku.
But it is a necessary step
before we can say
hello again, and we will.
I promise.
Master Roshi, friends,
I would ask that you
look after my grandson
in my absence.
You are now his family.
And Baba,
I appreciate this opportunity.
Yeah. Next time
you better not lose.
[GOHAN] You have a strong
heart and I'm proud of you.
No matter what happens in life,
always remember that.
[GOHAN] So long, everybody!
See you again in Other World!
Yeah, sounds great...
No offense, but I hope we
don't see you again too soon.
[laughing]
[GOKU] Grandpa?
Grandpa, I...
I hope you have
a nice trip back.
Until we meet again. Sayonara.
So long, Gohan.
Grandpa!
I know my tail is going
to grow back again,
and when it does,
I promise you I'll train it
to be stronger than ever before!
If you can grow it
as strong as your lungs,
you've got nothing
to worry about.
I'm telling your fortune
if anyone's interested.
Listen, crystal, hear my call!
Where can I find
the Seventh Dragon Ball?!
Tell me now, tell me true,
show me what I ask of you!
Let's see.
Huh... It's moving.
Moving where?
[BABA] Look into my
crystal ball. It's all there.
As you can plainly see,
the seventh Dragon Ball
is being transported
in that red automobile.
This is strange.
If the Dragon Ball
truly is in that car,
why doesn't it
show up on the radar?
Where is the car?
Please tell me.
I need to know!
Easy. Calm down.
It's headed in that direction.
It's about 200 miles away.
It's close.
Did you hear that, Upa?!
It won't be long now
and you'll be back together
with your father.
Great!
[NARRATOR] The location
of the last Dragon Ball
has been revealed.
Unfortunately, Goku must go
through Emperor Pilaf
and his destructive
Power Suits to get it.
The adventure continues,
next time on Dragon Ball!