[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku's fiancée, ChiChi received
a wedding dress from her father,
the Ox King.
ChiChi was honored to
accept the family heirloom.
Unfortunately, the happy
moment didn't last long,
as the Ox King's castle was
devastated by violent tremors.
[OX KING] I'll get the dress!
Goku, take ChiChi to safety.
[NARRATOR] Sheets of fire
erupted from the ground,
enveloping the castle in flames.
At the desperate request of
his future father-in-law,
Goku set out
to find the Bansho fan,
a powerful instrument able to
extinguish the raging blaze.
Fortuneteller Baba used
her crystal ball
to aid in the search,
learning the fan's location
was linked to an octagon.
Goku drained a pond
matching the shape
and discovered a pillar
covered in symbols,
similar to those found on a
poster owned by Master Roshi.
[NARRATOR] Goku and ChiChi
raced to Roshi's island,
but time was running out for
the Ox King and his kingdom.
[MAI]
Can you see anything?
[SHU] I see three rocks
that look like a face! Neat!
[MAI]
Shu!
[SHU humming]
[SHU]
Uh! There he is. I've got him!
Nice outfit. Ha.
We have proof.
The rumors were true.
The king is trapped!
Isn't there anything we can do?
Afraid not.
A rescue attempt is impossible
unless we control those flames.
[TURTLE humming]
Huh?
Hello there. I'm back!
That's nice... Who are you?
Goku.
[GOKU]
Don't you recognize me?
[TURTLE]
Uh... Uh...
Oh, Goku! It's really you!
I have changed a little.
That's an understatement.
Who's this?
I'm Goku's fiancée, ChiChi.
Really?
Is Roshi here?
Not quite. You're the first
one I've seen in a while.
He hasn't returned
from the tournament yet.
[GOKU, CHICHI gasp]
No.
[GOKU]
That's right.
I didn't think about how long it
would take them to get back.
They're on an airplane.
It could take hours!
Can I help you
with something then?
I'm trying to track
down the Bansho fan.
Bansho fan! I remember it well.
I yelled at Master Roshi
for using it as a coaster.
As usual, he never
listened to me.
I'm afraid he threw
it away, years ago.
I know, I know. It's okay.
We'll make another one.
Uh, from scratch?
Yes!
According to his sister, Master
Roshi has the instructions!
If he does, they would be
in his archives in his closet.
But I've never heard
him mention 'em.
We're running out of time!
All right. No need to shout.
Come on, hurry it up, guys!
I... am...
Ah.
--[GOKU] Up we go!
--[TURTLE] Watch the shell!
[TURTLE]
Uhh... No...
Uhm... No...
--[CHICHI] Eh.
--[TURTLE] Uh... Uh...
[TURTLE]
Sorry.
Hey! Here it is!
[CHICHI]
Huh?
Bansho... Bansho...
No, no. A-ha!
[TURTLE]
You were right.
[BOTH sigh]
Hmm.
According to this text,
the Bansho fan is an
all-purpose tool
that brings about a strong
wind as you fan once,
a cloud as you fan twice, and a
downpour as you fan three times.
Ingredients are as follows:
a... a feather of a Fire-Eater,
a mystical bird that
lives at the crater
of Mt. Kiwi, in the south.
Fire-Eater?
Mh-hm.
It's a pretty
mean-looking picture too.
--[GOKU] Let's go!
--[CHICHI laughs]
[CHICHI screams, laughs]
[GOKU]
Are you cold?
No, I'm all right.
Your back is warm.
[BOTH laughing]
[GOKU]
This looks like the place.
[CHICHI]
I think so.
It's so hot in here,
like a furnace.
ChiChi, watch your step
and follow me.
[CHICHI]
Mh-hm.
[GOKU] What a strange
sounding creature!
[CHICHI] Almost like something
from a fairy tale.
[GOKU] Too bad it's the only
clue we have to go on.
What's wrong?
Can't you hear it?
Huh?
[BEAST growling]
What's making that awful noise?
Ah! The Fire-Eater!
[BEAST growling]
It's getting closer!
[CHICHI whimpering]
[GOKU]
Be quiet, ChiChi. It could be--
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Stay very still, ChiChi.
--[CHICHI wimpering]
--[BEAST growling]
[growls]
I apologize if we woke you up.
[screams]
[BEAST growling]
[GOKU]
There, there.
[CHICHI sighs]
We have uninvited guests.
Do you think they're also
looking for the bird?
[MAI]
No, they're sight-seeing!
Of course they're
looking for the bird!
What if they've already found
it? We'd better follow them!
[screams]
[BEAST growls]
[SHU laughs]
[SHU]
Don't worry. He's a pushover.
[SHU laughs]
I apologize if we woke you up.
Huh?
[BEAST growls]
[MAI, SHU scream]
[BOTH scream]
[CHICHI whimpering]
[screams]
Mai! Help me!
[BOTH screaming]
--[breaking rocks]
--[CHICHI screams]
[GOKU]
ChiChi!
[CHICHI]
Goku!
[sighs]
Are you all right?
I'm fine, but... what's that?
You're safe!
[CHICHI]
Come down here and say that!
[GOKU]
What's wrong?
Hmm?
[yells]
I've never seen such a big egg!
I have a strong feeling it
belongs to the Fire-Eater.
[SCIENTIST]
Hey, what are you doing?
Hands off my egg!
Goku, please hurry!
[GOKU]
You laid this egg?
[SCIENTIST] Are you crazy?
It belongs to the Fire-Eater.
[GOKU, CHICHI cheer]
[SCIENTIST]
Settle down! Who are you?
Hello, I'm Goku.
I'm ChiChi.
We're trying to find
the Fire-Eater, sir.
Where's the bird
that laid this egg?
[SCIENTIST]
Nowhere.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[SCIENTIST]
They perished a long time ago.
[BOTH sigh]
[SCIENTIST] It must be forty
years now. Hard to believe.
This mountain suffered
a huge eruption.
It took the Fire-Eaters
by surprise.
There was no time to escape.
They were crushed by
falling rocks while attempting
to find a path to safety.
The Fire-Eaters were
glorious creatures.
This egg is all that
remains of their legacy.
[CHICHI] I can't believe the egg
survived for 40 years.
[SCIENTIST] The heat produced by
this volcano has kept it alive.
It is an ironic twist of fate.
It's nothing short of a miracle.
When is it going to hatch?
[SCIENTIST sighs]
Who knows? The heat
keeps it alive,
but there's no telling
if it will ever hatch.
We're back to square one.
Baba may know what to do.
[rumbling]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL yell]
[SCIENTIST]
Who are you?
We are here for the egg.
[SCIENTIST]
Oh?
We've been monitoring
your progress, doctor.
I must say, I'm impressed.
We never thought you'd find it.
And now, we'll take
it from here.
Huh?
You're here to steal the egg?
[SCIENTIST]
Don't be silly.
You can't remove the egg
from its environment.
[SHU]
Hm. Allow me to introduce
the genius responsible
for our bold mission.
His majesty is the most
feared man in the underworld.
A true titan of terror,
the man I call sire!
It is an honor
and privilege to serve...
[SHU] The one, the only,
Emperor Pilaf!
Aw, you again.
You know him?
[PILAF]
Hm. Such a beautiful sight.
There is nothing more precious
than a one-of-a-kind.
This egg is going
to make me zillions!
And with that much money,
the entire world will be yours.
[PILAF]
And then some!
[laughs]
The last one and
it's mine, all mine!
It doesn't belong to you!
Ah? Shu, come here!
[PILAF whispering]
Hey, girl!
The name's ChiChi!
I have a secret.
--[MAI grunts]
--[CHICHI yelps]
[BOTH gasp]
[PILAF, SHU, MAI laugh]
That was easy.
So are my terms: the girl
in exchange for the egg! Eh?
Hey. Nice hat there.
You look like a baby.
[PILAF chuckles]
[laughs]
--[GOKU laughing]
--Ha! Don't underestimate me!
This egg will be mine!
I will stop at
nothing to possess it!
[GOKU laughing]
I've seen his face
before, but where?
I know what you mean.
He looks familiar.
Tell me who he is.
His name... is Goku.
Goku?
Eh? Goku?
[SHU, MAI gasp]
[BOTH]
Goku!
I'm tired of playing games.
So, you two get rid
of that annoying girl.
[sighs]
Have... mercy!
Too late!
--[CHICHI grunts]
--[MAI, CHU yelp]
[MAI, SHU groan]
[PILAF growls]
[grunting]
[PILAF grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[yelling]
I recognize that hair style!
It's...
[PILAF]
...Goku!
[PILAF screaming]
[MAI, SHU]
Emperor, wait!
Well, we'd better be going.
Good luck, Mister.
Hmm. Same to you.
I hope your egg hatches.
[laughs]
[rumbling]
[yells]
--[GOKU gasps]
--[whimpers] Not again!
[CHICHI whimpering]
--[CHICHI yelps]
--[GOKU, SCIENTIST sputter]
[BOTH grunting]
--[CHICHI whimpers]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[GOKU gasps]
--Oh my.
I... I'm dreaming.
Is it possible one has survived?
I'd say so.
It's a Fire-Eater!
[screeching]
[whimpers]
[yelp] Watch out!
[screeching]
[screeching continues]
[chirps]
[CHICHI] I think it's time
for us to leave now.
Nonsense. She just
needs nourishment.
Don't worry, girl.
Your baby is still alive.
[BOTH gasp]
[screeching]
[BOTH gasping]
[whimpering]
[BOTH laugh]
[BOTH screech]
--[CHICHI sighs]
--[GOKU chuckles]
[CHICHI laughs, gasps]
Time to leave!
[SCIENTIST groans]
[ALL panting]
[ALL scream]
Ka... Me...
Haa... Mee...
Ha!
[CHICHI panting]
[FIRE-EATER screeches]
[ALL panting]
[SCIENTIST]
Oh?
[FIRE-EATERS screeching]
[ALL gasping]
[BOTH sigh]
Ah! But what about the feather?
[gasp] Oh wait!
[BOTH gasp]
We did it!
--[CHICHI] Feathers!
--[GOKU laughs] Yeah!
[CHICHI, GOKU laughing]
[CHICHI]
Huh?
[GOKU]
Uh?
[CHICHI]
Huh?
--[GOKU] Huh?
--[CHICHI gasps]
I don't understand.
Maybe we did something wrong.
What are you doing?
[BOTH gasp]
We were told we could
make a Bansho fan
out of the
Fire-Eater's feathers.
Oh, brother!
That's why you wanted the
Fire-Eater's feathers?
Ha, ha! You're on
a fool's errand!
The Fire-Eater lives on flames.
If its feathers put them out,
how would it survive?
You have a good point.
[ROSHI]
Nothing in this book works!
I couldn't decipher
that crazy code!
I only wrote the book
to impress some girl.
[groans]
--[CHICHI] Hmm.
--[GOKU] Uh?
You were right. We're
back where we started.
Bansho fan...
Oh, yes! I remember.
I know where it is.
--[CHICHI shrieks, laughs]
--You do?
[SCIENTIST] Yes, but finding
it will be a challenge.
The Bansho fan is frozen in
an iceberg, far north of here.
[GOKU]
Thank you! Let's go, ChiChi.
[laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[CHICHI]
Goodbye!
[SCIENTIST thinking]
Kids riding clouds.
Now I've seen it all.
Too bad it's a two-seater.
I could use a lift.
[NARRATOR]
With a new clue,
Goku and ChiChi rush north in
search of the Bansho Fan.
Will they find it,
or some other dark peril?
Don't miss the next
episode of Dragon Ball!