[NARRATOR] Goku and Bulma
have their five Dragon Balls,
and are crossing the desert
in search of the sixth.
[NARRATOR] But a treacherous
plan is being hatched to
spoil their mission.
[liquid pouring]
Let's get going, Puar.
We can't let those three slip
through our fingers.
Huh? But what about the girl,
Yamcha?
Remember?
[chuckling]
Leave that to me.
I've got a plan.
So, why didn't you tell
us before that you had this
camper Dyno-Cap, Oolong? Hmm?
Well you didn't exactly ask me,
now did you?
Besides, I didn't want
those bandits to steal it.
[chomping]
[OOLONG] Kid, watch
yourself, you're gonna choke.
Mmm...This is good.
I hope I see Yamcha again.
He was so shy and so handsome...
[BULMA] Does this
place have a tub?
[OOLONG] Yeah, right in there.
[BULMA] Huh. To
tell you the truth,
I'm used to much
nicer accommodations.
[OOLONG] Then why don't you try
a luxury hotel down the road?
I'm sure there are lots of
'em out here in the desert!
It's just that it's so small.
Well it ain't no palace,
but I don't see any
royalty around either,
get it?
Now what are you looking for?
[BULMA] Peepholes.
Hey! What kind of place
you think I'm runnin'?!
Well, I wouldn't
put it past you.
What?
[BULMA] You little perv.
[chuckling]
[OOLONG] I'll let you
win the battle, sister,
but I'm gonna win the war.
[crickets chirping]
[mechanical springing]
[beeping]
[MAI] Emperor. Spy pods
are now in position.
We are ready to put
operation "Desert Dragon Bomb"
into effect. Over.
Good. Proceed as planned,
Agent Mai. Base out.
[MAI] Let's go!
[MAI] Come on!
[beeping]
[SHU] It's set to go
off in four minutes.
[MAI] Huh?
[running footsteps]
Shu, somebody's out there!
[SHU] Hm?
Let's get out of here.
[SHU] Mai, I think
we have a problem.
The bomb is stuck to my hand.
[squealing]
This isn't good, Shu!
What should I do?!
[running footsteps]
You better wait here.
I'll go get help.
[SHU] Hey, wait for me!
[YAMCHA] Mm-hmm...a
double-decker camper.
I'll bet we can get a decent
price for a rig like that.
But what about the girl?
[chuckling]
Easy. All we have to do
is find a way to lure her
out of there for a few minutes.
Then we sneak in and
rob them blind! Ha ha ha!
[PUAR] You're
starting to scare me.
You think we're safe out here?
Don't worry! The worst
thing that could happen to us
is they take our stuff.
That's it, huh? Well I
don't know if you've noticed,
but I've got some
very serious cargo here.
You're not worried,
'cause you don't
have anything worth stealing.
Yeah-huh. My Dragon Ball.
Huh? Dragon Ball?
What's that?
[GOKU] Well, Bulma asked
me not to show you,
but...I guess it's okay.
Neat, huh?
--[water running]
--[BULMA humming]
[BULMA humming]
Okay, she's right above us.
[PUAR] Master, can you see if
the other two are with her?
Hang on.
[YAMCHA stuttering]
[YAMCHA screaming]
[YAMCHA whimpering]
Yamcha?! What happened?!
Are you all right?!
[BULMA] Hmm?
Is something out there?
Hm? Oh well.
I hate turning
into a bowl of mush
everytime I see a girl!
It's not your fault...
[PUAR and YAMCHA] Hmm?
I think I hear something.
[OOLONG] Are you sure it's true?
It's the pig
and the kid. Hmph.
[OOLONG] So, when you get all
seven Dragon Balls together,
the Dragon appears
and grants a wish?
[GOKU] Uh-huh. Yep, that's
right.
[OOLONG] Any wish
you can think of?
Guess so.
That's what Bulma said.
So, how many more
Dragon Balls do you need?
Just two.
[OOLONG] Heh! We're on to
something really big here,
Goku old pal!
--Come on.
--Right!
Well, it seems
we hit the jackpot!
Yeah?
Puar, you know what
this means, don't you?!
What Yamcha?
I will never be shy
around women again! Never!
But Yamcha, if you
could have any wish,
then you could rule the world
and have all the riches in it.
Come on! How long
have you been with me?
[PUAR] It's been two years,
one month, and three days.
After all this time,
I thought you really
would have
known me by now.
[PUAR] I thought so too...
Well, my furry
friend, you don't.
I have no aspirations
to rule the world. Understand?
I think I do...
[YAMCHA] No... I want what no
riches in the world can buy...
Don't you see that one
day I'd like to get married?
Or at least be
able to ask a girl out
on one single, lousy date!
See what happens
when you don't have
an afternoon nap, Master?
From now on,
we have only those
Dragon Balls in our sights!
We'll get them. Mark my words.
You know, kid?
We need to cut Bulma out.
That's all there is to it.
But Bulma and I are partners.
Why would you
want to cut her out?
Look, kid, she's
a girl and we're guys.
And we're going to want
to wish for some guy things.
Like, a harem with
three-hundred girls!
Golly, why would you
wanna have three-hundred girls?
Huh? How's that, kid?
Well, can you imagine
what it would be like
having three-hundred
Bulmas to listen to?
How dare you talk
behind my back, Goku?!
I was just, uh...
Oh, nevermind.
Oolong, do you have
any extra pajamas?
Oh, like mine
would fit you.
[BULMA] So what am I
supposed to wear to bed, then?
What am I,
your butler?!
Well, with that
hat you look like one.
[BULMA] Or a limo driver,
or something.
[OOLONG] Here you go. This cold
juice will calm your nerves.
You can be a sweet swine,
can't you?
More than you'll ever know.
Aw, thank you.
[snickering]
[sniffing]
Eww, this stuff's gross!
[OOLONG] It's for,
uh, health nuts.
It's, uh, supposed
to make you strong.
Oh well.
Down the hatch.
[snickering]
I do feel stronger!
You want some, Oolong?
Oh, for me?
I, uh, had mine already.
So where do I sleep?
I'm tired...
Just go right up
those stairs there.
[BULMA] Good night.
And you better
not come up here!
Or I'll just have to make
the 'piggy' sound again,
and you'll be going "Wee, wee
wee! All the way home"! Get it?
Gotcha.
[BULMA] And since you're
not doing anything,
I want my clothes
cleaned by morning.
Right.
[OOLONG grumbling]
Boy, the way
she was nagging me,
you would think we
were married or something.
I'll never understand women.
Huh?
[snoring]
[OOLONG] That sleeping powder
works faster than I thought!
[OOLONG] Stealing the Dragon
Balls is gonna be a cinch
with these kids knocked out!
[SHU] Uh-oh!
[MAI] Hurry, Shu!
Something's wrong!
It won't stop!
It's gonna blow in
less than a minute!
[MAI screaming]
Oh, what am I gonna do?
I'm too young to blow up...
What happened?
Tell me, Shu!
Nothing to worry about,
Mai.
I reset it for eight
o'clock tomorrow morning.
Then: boom.
[GOKU snoring]
[chuckling]
[OOLONG] I bet the Dragon
Balls are upstairs...
and I know the first
place I'm gonna look.
It's all clear, Yamcha.
All right, Puar.
This is it. You know what to do?
Uh-huh!
[lock clicking]
[chuckling]
What's that?!
This kid is really zonked out!
I wonder where the
other two have gone?
I guess they're upstairs.
Puar, I want you to
change into this kid here
and lure the
others outside, okay?
Okay!
How could Goku be awake
after that dose I gave him?!
[OOLONG] I don't get it!
I put enough in his drink
to knock out a horse!
[OOLONG] If that little imp
catches me up here, he's sure to
squeal to Bulma and
she'll fry my bacon good!
I gotta think of something fast!
Oh, I know!
Oh, hi, Goku!
You scared me!
[PUAR] Hey.
Where's Oolong?
Oolong?
I thought he went for a
walk? I thought he was back!
[PUAR] Hey, I know!
Let's go outside
and look for him!
There's something I wanna
show you out there, anyway.
Well, um, all right.
[OOLONG muttering]
[PUAR] Looks like Oolong
hasn't come back yet!
[giggling]
[OOLONG] I have a feeling
he's pretty close by!
With her out of the way,
nothing can stop me!
Strange, though. In the daylight
she seemed much prettier...
[GOKU snoring]
[YAMCHA] Ah-ha!
I betcha I know what's
under here: Dragon Balls!
Odd. They seem...
kinda flimsy...
I'm freezing!
What do you want to show me?!
It's right up here.
Now, watch real close!
What in the world?!
Tricked you good, huh?
You wanna make a bet?!
Oolong?! But--!
[screaming]
Master!
Come back here!
[whimpering]
Are you okay?!
Not... Dragon Balls...
My poor master!
[OOLONG] Hey!
Where are you?!
[PUAR] Come on, Yamcha!
Let's go! Come on, come on!
[YAMCHA] Not... Dragon Balls...
Not... Dragon Balls...
It's like a thieves
convention here!
[birds cawing]
[GOKU yawning]
It's about time.
Oh, good morning.
Yeah, for you, maybe.
Nice sleep?
Huh?
Oh... I have a
terrible headache...
Hey, Oolong, did you
get my clothes clean yet?
Sorry, I've been a little busy.
What?! What do you mean 'busy'?!
This is serious!
I don't have any
clothes to wear!
I mean busy saving
your hides from Yamcha.
Yamcha?
[BULMA] Wow, he came back!
Were you nice to him?
Yamcha's real shy, you know?
I think I'm gonna puke.
What did you say?!
Nothing.
And if you really need clothes,
there's one outfit in
the drawer upstairs.
Why didn't you just
say so in the first place?!
Hmph!
Yeah. come to think of it,
maybe three-hundred girls
is a few too many, little buddy.
[GOKU] So, does that mean
you're changing your mind
about the harem thing?
[OOLONG] Yup!
Gee, you sure are one smart pig,
Oolong.
[stomach growling]
I'm hungry.
You are always hungry, kid.
[beeping]
[PILAF] What?! You
two failed me again?!
Next time I'll know
better than to get my spies
from the want ads!
Sorry, sir. But we've
already reprogrammed the bomb.
It's set to blow at eight.
What? At eight?
[PILAF] Why, that's
just an hour away.
All right, but no more mistakes!
[MAI] Yes, sir.
Agent Mai out.
[chomping]
A month's supply of food gone!
Hey, what's this? Easter?!
This is no outfit,
it's a costume!
And I look ridiculous in it,
Oolong!
Well, tough luck!
That's all I've got.
My stock of women's
clothes is down this month.
Hmph. You know, there's
something not quite right
about you, Oolong, but I
just can't quite figure it out.
I'm a pig?
Whew, me too!
Ha ha, that was great!
[engine humming]
[OOLONG] So why am I driving?
I just hate driving!
[BULMA] Oh, quit
your complaining.
I'm putting on my make-up.
Kid, this girl's
a pain in the neck.
Tell me if you see Yamcha.
[tires squealing]
Yeah, we'll keep our
fingers crossed, Bulma.
Oh, can't wait to see him.
Is that him?
[YAMCHA laughing]
Wow!
That Yamcha's such a hunk!
[YAMCHA] Steady Puar.
That's it!
Oh!
He's looking right at me!
Uh-oh.
[BULMA screaming]
What's the big idea?!
Are you two nuts?!
[PUAR] Don't worry
about the girl, master.
I bet she got
knocked out in the crash.
Okay. Game's up.
Listen. Now give me the
Dragon Balls or you will die!
Goku,
how does that goon know
about the Dragon Balls?!
Stop your gawking
and hand them over, now!
I'll hand over this!
Goku, he's got a gun!
I couldn't possibly
turn down a fight
with Gohan's grandson, Puar.
So, you little runt,
you want another spanking
from my Wolf's Fang Fist?!
I was hungry last time,
but now my stomach's full!
[blows landing]
Atta boy!
Have you had enough yet?
Yamcha, let's
get out--Oh no!
Look at your teeth!
[YAMCHA screaming]
[YAMCHA] Oh no, look at me!
Now I'll never get a date!
[YAMCHA] I won't forget
this, kid! I'll be back!
[engine revving]
That was strange.
Wow, Goku!
You were phenomenal!
You really showed him!
Thanks, Oolong.
I think we'd better
go check on Bulma.
[OOLONG] Hope she's in better
shape than our ride...
I guess we
underestimated that kid.
He knows his stuff.
But we can use that
to our advantage, Puar.
We'll just let them find
all of the Dragon Balls.
Then, when they have all
seven, we'll make our strike.
Yamcha, you are the greatest!
You are!
[YAMCHA screaming]
Looks like that
bomb did the trick.
Those poor shmucks
never knew what hit 'em.
That's strange.
It blew before eight o'clock.
Don't worry about it.
Pilaf probably got
those bombs on sale.
[MAI] I'm going to check
inside for the Dragon Balls.
[beeping]
I wonder how
Bulma stayed out of
trouble before she met me.
Hey, why don't you let
me carry her little buddy?
I'd be happy to give
her - er, you a hand.
[chuckling]
[YAMCHA] Hey, you guys!
Over here!
Ah! Look, kid!
It's him!
[YAMCHA] Wait, wait, wait,
wait! Hello there!
We were talking and, uh, oh
well, we really don't want to
have any hard
feelings between us.
Ha, it was a fair
fight, so, here you go!
What's the catch?
There is no catch, my friends.
Goodbye!
Have a good day!
Man. What's up with him?
I guess deep down,
he's really a good guy.
Yeah, bologna.
I don't buy it.
I better check
this thing for bombs.
Sometimes you have
to trust in people.
[OOLONG] Yeah, right.
[beeping]
[PUAR] There they go, Yamcha.
Your homing device is working!
[explosion]
Shu... are we still alive...?
I think so...
[NARRATOR] Even with the odds
stacked against them, our heroes
continue their trek across
the desert in search of the
elusive Dragon Balls.
What perils await them?
[NARRATOR] Will they survive?
Find out on the next episode of
Dragon Ball.