[NARRATOR]
Previously, on Dragon Ball:
News of Goku's
crash landing spread
through the ranks of
the Red Ribbon Army.
What?
There's a plane down?
[WHITE] It's got to
be the missing jet
headquarters radioed about!
According to the report, there
was a boy flying that plane...
[SOLDIER B] There's no
sign of him here, sir.
Just a shattered robot.
[WHITE] He's out
there somewhere.
Find him!
[SOLDIER C]
Hey, I think I got something.
Look at this!
[SOLDIER B]
Looks like tracks.
Hmm.
Something's been dragged
outta here... or someone.
[WHITE] Tracks?!
You're calling in
to report tracks?!
You imbecile!!
Stop wasting my time
and follow that trail
before the snow covers it up!
[SOLDIER B] Yes sir...
Move out!
[SUNO panting]
[WHITE] Report, sergeant.
Any sign of the boy?
[SOLDIER B] Not yet, sir.
It's kinda hard to see on
account of all the snow.
[WHITE]
It's a blizzard, you idiot!
Of course it's hard to see!
Which means that kid
couldn't have gotten far!
Now, move your tank
and find him!
[SOLDIER B] Yes, sir!
All right, people! Listen up!
We're rolling out.
Look sharp and follow my lead!
[SUNO knocking]
Mother! Mother!
Come quick!
[MOTHER]
Suno!
What are you doing out
in weather like this?
You'll catch
your death of cold!
I found something, mother.
[MOTHER gasps]
[MOTHER]
Oh my!
It's a boy.
He fell from a plane.
That's a matter for
the authorities, dear.
[SUNO] But I think
he's still alive.
[MOTHER]
Huh?!
[WHITE gulping]
[WHITE sighs]
[WHITE] How can one little boy
evade an entire army?
Maybe I should fire my soldiers
and hire him instead.
[WHITE chuckles]
Crafty little bug.
I'm going to
enjoy squishing him.
[GOKU snoring]
[SUNO] He looks so peaceful
sitting there.
Can we keep him?
[MOTHER] He's not a pet, Suno.
[SUNO] He's better.
He's a boy!
Now I'll have someone
to play with!
[GOKU groans]
[SUNO gasps]
I think he's waking up!
[MOTHER] What?
[GOKU groans]
[SUNO giggles]
Hi.
Who're... you?
I'm Suno.
I'm cold.
Yeah, you were frozen!
Here. Drink this.
You'll feel better.
Ahh... Thanks!
[GOKU slurps and yells]
Silly... you have
to blow on it first.
[SUNO laughs]
[MOTHER] You know,
you gave us quite a scare.
If you'd been out
there any longer,
I don't think we would've
been able to thaw you out.
How did I get here anyway?
[SONU sighs] Me.
I found you in the woods.
Oh, I guess I don't
remember... but thanks.
Oh, no problem...
I was coming home anyway...
Yep, you'd probably be dead
right now if it weren't for me.
Stuck out there, frozen stiff.
So tell us about yourself.
Do you have a name to go
with that handsome haircut?
[GOKU slurps] My name's Goku.
I came here looking
for a Dragon Ball.
Boy, this is good!
[SUNO gasps] Dragon Ball?!
[GOKU] Huh?
[SUNO yells]
[MOTHER] Are you
a Red Ribbon soldier?
[MOTHER and SUNO whimper]
[GOKU] What?
No... I'm no soldier.
But I did run into
some before I came here.
They were mean, too.
[SOLDIER B whimpers]
Stop! Stop!!
[SOLDIER C grunting
[SOLDIER B]
Soldier, look in the back,
and see if there's
an extra pair of shorts.
[SOLDIER C] Yes, sir.
[SOLDIER B] Coordinate X1
appears to be a dead end.
Repeat, X1 is a dead end.
We're turning East
to coordinate X2. Copy?
[SOLDIER C]
Turning East to coordinate X2!
--[SOLDIER B] Wait!
--[SOLDIER C] Huh?
[SOLDIER B] Cancel that order.
[SOLDIER B chuckles]
[ammo rounds drop on floor]
[COUPLE whimpers]
[SOLDIER B]
He's not here.
[SOLDIER C] Granny...
[SOLDIER C]
What big eyes you have.
[OLD WOMAN] Please...
don't hurt us!
[SOLDIER C] Listen!
If you happen to spot a little
boy, you be sure to let us know.
There are other houses
to search in this cesspool.
Let's go!
[COUPLE whimpering]
Wait!
These Red Ribbon guys
must be the ones that're
after the Dragon Balls!
I wonder why they
want them so bad?
[SUNO] I don't know.
Maybe for the same
reason you do.
But I'm only
looking for one.
It belongs to my grandpa...
Here, I'll show you.
[GOKU] This is a Dragon Ball.
That's a--
Dragon Ball?
[GOKU]
Mmhmm.
Wow... it's beautiful.
[GOKU] This isn't the one
I'm looking for, though...
The one I want has
four stars on it.
[SUNO]
Maybe the Army wants them
because they're
worth a lot of money!
[MOTHER] It certainly
looks valuable...
Sure, it looks really nice,
but there's more
to it than that.
It's got magic powers...
There are seven of these in all,
and if you bring them together
then the Great Dragon comes
out and gives you a wish!
[MOTHER sighs]
[SUNO] A dragon?
Yep!
[GOKU] I've only seen it once--
well, heard it mostly.
I was trapped inside
a castle at the time.
But I'll tell you
what I remember.
As soon as the Dragon Balls
were placed together,
the sky got covered up
by big dark clouds...
and the balls started to glow
and make this weird noise!
Then they shot out this
big bright light into the sky!
It was brighter than the sun!
[SUNO] Wait!
I thought you said you
couldn't see anything?
[MOTHER] Hush, Suno!
Let him finish.
[GOKU]
Anyway, the bright light
started to move
around really fast
and then it turned into
the shape of a Dragon.
It was huge!
The biggest thing
I've ever seen!
[DRAGON roars]
[SUNO] So, what
did you wish for?
[GOKU] Me?
I didn't wish for anything!
[SUNO] You didn't?
So how do you know
it really works?
[GOKU] Well, I didn't
get to make a wish,
but my friend Oolong did!
I'm a coward.
I don't want to be the hero!
I don't want to save the day!
This stinks!
[GOKU] And do you
know what he wished for?
[SUNO]
What? Tell me! Tell me!
The world's most
comfortable pair of underwear!
[OOLONG]
Oooh!
[OOLONG snickers]
Underwear?!
Why would anyone wish for
something so stupid, huh?!
[GOKU] It wasn't my wish...
I'm sure... someone... um, oh...
Hey!
There was another guy
who wanted to rule the world!
Oh wow!
[MOTHER] That's it!
[SUNO and GOKU]
Huh?
That must be the reason
the Red Ribbon Army is trying to
find all the Dragon Balls...
These are the kind of men
who would want
to take over the world.
I hope not, because
I think there's another
ball near here, and if--
We know.
My father and the others are
helping them search for it.
Your father?
I guess the army didn't
have enough soldiers
to search an area this big
so they forced many of
the villagers to help them.
If there aren't that many,
why don't the villagers
fight the soldiers?
Because they're too strong.
And they've got weapons!
[MOTHER] What's more, they've
kidnapped our village chief,
and they're holding him
hostage in their tower.
And if we don't
do what they say...
They're going to hurt him.
[GOKU]
Oh...
Maybe we should just
give them what they're after...
So they'll leave
our village in peace...
Yes...
Maybe if you give them
the Dragon Ball you have,
the army will go away
and leave us alone!
It's not even
the one you want!
[GOKU] Right!
[SUNO] Thank you.
[GOKU] Don't worry.
I'll beat them.
[MOTHER and SUNO gasp]
[GOKU] It's the least
I can do for all your help.
[SUNO] What are you, crazy?
They have big tanks and guns!
And you're just a little boy!
[ALL gasps]
[SUNO gasps]
What was that noise?
I-It m-might be the...
Quick.
You'd better hide somewhere.
Oh, first I've gotta
use the bathroom!
[SOLDIER B] Knock-knock.
[MOTHER yelps]
[SUNO and MOTHER whimper]
[SOLDIER B]
I'm looking for a boy!
[MOTHER] There's no one
here but my daughter and me.
--[toilet flushes]
--[SUNO and MOTHER gasp]
[MOTHER and SUNO yell]
[SOLDIER B giggles]
No!
[SUNO whimpers]
[GOKU groans]
Ow!
[SOLDIER B yells]
[GOKU] Is this your father?
[SUNO] No! They're
Red Ribbon soldiers!
Run for it!
[GOKU] Oh, well in that case...
Fight!
You little--
Hiyah!
[SOLDIERS B and C groan]
[MOTHER and SUNO gasp]
[SUNO] Are you all right?!
You just punched those soldiers!
Actually it was
6 punches and...
One, two, three, four--
yeah, four kicks.
That was... unbelievable.
Don't be silly.
You just saw me do it.
Okay, I'll go get your chief
now and then we can eat lunch!
[SUNO] Bu--wait!
Unusual boy...
I know...
I hope we see him again.
[MOTHER and SUNO yell]
[GOKU] I-It's kinda...
c-cold outside!
[GOKU whimpering]
[MOTHER] Here.
Try and stay warm.
[SUNO] I'll get you some
of my clothes to wear.
Goku, listen to me...
This is foolish.
Do you have any
idea what's out there?
Sure, bad guys.
[SUNO giggles]
Hey, see how these fit.
[MOTHER] I'm afraid we haven't
told you the whole story...
[MOTHER] The Red Ribbon Army
is holding our village chief in
a place called Muscle Tower.
It's the Army General's
command post.
It's got solid stone walls
fortified with guns and guards
and who knows
what other dangers.
Several of the village men
have already tried to
rescue our chief.
Not one of them made it
out of the tower alive.
[GOKU] Sounds scary.
I wonder how long it'll
take me to get there?
[GOKU giggles]
This feels great!
Listen. Take care of yourself...
and don't take chances.
Don't worry about me...
I'll be fine.
[GOKU] Say, what do you call
this cold, white mushy stuff?
Its... called snow.
Amazing!
Well, gotta run.
See ya! Bye!
Vroom!
Do you really think he can
defeat the army, mother?
He thinks he can,
but so did your father.
[whistling]
[SOLDIER X] Huh?
[SOLDIER X]
Hey! What...
What the--
[GOKU yells]
[gunfire]
[GOKU]
Huh?
[SOLDIER X] Hey!
Where do you think
you're going, kid?
[GOKU] I'm going to the tower.
Huh?
Oh, got some
pressing business there, do ya?
Why don't you run
home to your mommy.
[GOKU] Are you soldiers
of the Red Ribbon Army?
Yeah...that
would be us, kiddo.
[GOKU] In that case--
Fight me!
[SOLDIER D and
SOLDIER E chuckle] Huh?
[GOKU yells]
[SOLDIER X]
Hmm?
[GOKU laughs]
[SOLDIER X yells]
Oof!
[SOLDIER D]
Huh?
[GOKU]
Hiyah!
[SOLDIERS H and G]
Huh?
Intruder!
[GOKU yells]
[BEAR] General White, there's
a kid storming the tower!
[WHITE] What?!
[GOKU yells]
Heh!
Like a lamb to the slaughter...
Fire! Fire now!
[GOKU] Power Pole extend!
[GOKU] Power Pole retract!
[GOKU chuckles]
Well, I am impressed
little lamb...
Come on up.
I'll be right here
waiting for you.
[WHITE chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Now that our hero
has made it onto
the mysterious Muscle Tower,
what peril awaits him inside?
Will he be able to rescue
the village chief?
And can even Goku defeat
the diabolical General White
and his hideous agenda?
Find out on the next thrilling
episode of Dragon Ball!