[NARRATOR] In search of their
sixth Dragon Ball, our three
adventurers, Bulma, Goku
and Oolong, now make their
way toward Fire Mountain,
the legendary home of a
terrible giant: the Ox-King.
How much longer
until we get there?
Not long enough!
[BULMA] Are you still scared
of that silly, old legend?
[BULMA] It's not real, you know.
I mean, listen to yourself!
[BULMA] Seriously, how
could a whole mountain
really be on fire?
[OOLONG] Great! I'm stuck
with a couple of non-believers.
Well, you just wait until
you see it for yourselves!
[BULMA] I gotta admit it is
getting hotter all of a sudden!
[panting]
Look at the sunset!
Is it ever bright!
Oh, wow! Eww.
I gotta brush my teeth...
[OOLONG] That isn't the sun, you
idiots, that's Fire Mountain!
No way!
I can't believe it!
Better ease back,
my friend.
We don't want to
be spotted just yet.
[PUAR] Right!
[SHU] In a way, I'm
glad we're almost there,
but in a way, I'm not.
[MAI] How're we
going to tell Pilaf
we didn't get the Dragon Balls?
[SHU] I don't know. I'm scared.
Yeah, just once
I'd like to hear that
little mutant encourage us
with words of appreciation.
You mean like
"Shu, Mai, just relax!
Some failures are to be
expected in the spy business!"
You are too kind,
oh wise Emperor!
Let's face it, Shu,
our goose is cooked!
Guess I'd better update my will.
[MAI] I just hope he
hasn't installed his new
"Do-It-Yourself
Torture Chamber" yet.
So, in other words,
you have failed me once again!
You could put
it that way, sire.
Yes, I guess
you could say that.
Well, this is
the spy business.
Some failures
are to be expected.
So relax! Eat! Good work!
You fools! You know I
don't greet failure with a
pat on the back!
[squealing]
[PILAF] You must pay for this!
[giggling]
[crying]
[SHU] We're toast!
[PILAF] Why, you imbeciles!
Do you think I enjoy doing this?
[giggling]
[thunder]
[screaming]
That was a shocking experience,
don't you think?
Yeah, a real charge.
Let's hope you two
morons have learned your lesson!
Well, there's Fire Mountain!
[BULMA] Wow! I've
never seen anything like it!
[GOKU] Oohh...
[BULMA] Uh-huh...
[OOLONG] I don't know about
you guys, but I've seen enough.
[OOLONG] I'm ready to go!
We have to get the
Dragon Ball first, Oolong.
No silly bonfire's
gonna scare me away!
A towering mountain
engulfed in eternal flames
doesn't scare you,
huh? Well it scares
the sausage out of me! Besides,
the evil Ox-King lives there
and he'll have our heads!
[BULMA] I bet he's got the ball!
[OOLONG] Yeah, I'm sure it's up
there, probably in his castle.
[OOLONG] And it's all yours.
Just get past the fiercest
giant in the world and
pass through that wall
of flames there, and
then you can have it!
[BULMA] Does he live
up there in the castle?
[OOLONG] He did, but
they say even he can't pass
through those flames.
So then,
why did he start the fire?
No, no!
He didn't start it, kid.
He paid some magical wizard to
create a fire to protect his
castle from thieves, right?
And then it raged out of
control, and he's been stuck
on the outside ever since!
You sure know a lot about it!
[OOLONG] I was a
tour guide for the local
Chamber of Commerce,
okay? And I just remembered,
I forgot to clock out,
so, see you later, ha ha!
You're the biggest
coward I know!
[OOLONG] Well, I know
why you're not scared,
you think Goku's
gonna protect you!
But he's no match
for the Ox-King!
My Grandpa taught me
how to be fearless,
so I'm not scared.
[OOLONG] Yeah? Well
I'll show you what my
grandpa taught me, squirt!
Hey!
Let's let him
get a head start!
[BULMA] You get
back here, you...
[growling]
[BULMA] Piggy!
[BULMAR] Piggy!
[intense diarrhea]
[BULMA and GOKU] Piggy! Piggy!
--[BULMA] Piggy!
--[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] Piggy!
Look, Yamcha!
They're on the move again.
You're right, Puar,
and they're heading straight for
Fire Mountain. I bet that
means the sixth Dragon Ball
is up there in the
Ox-King's castle.
What?! Oh, well that
Dragon Ball's definitely lost!
So you don't think
they have a chance?
[PUAR] Actually, they have
two chances: slim and none!
That Dragon Ball's
as good as gone.
Well, I suppose
you're probably right,
but let's stick
around for the show.
And just what
show is that, Master?
[YAMCHA] Come on, that kid Goku
is so confident I imagine he'll
try and take on the
Ox-King. Don't you agree?
Mm-hmm. I suppose so.
And there you have
it, my furry, little friend!
We finally get a chance
to watch poor, little Goku
get torn limb from limb!
[screaming]
Huh?
What?!
[screaming]
Oh no! Somebody help!
[fleash slicing]
[screaming]
Gross, look what I've done!
I chopped his head right off!
Now I've seen everything!
I don't think she even
had her eyes open, do you?
[crying]
Hey, nice work.
I was told to never
talk to strangers!
Hey, watch out!
[GIRL screams]
That girl's dangerous!
All right, Puar, we've wasted
enough time here already.
We'd better get
back on the road.
That girl was real cute,
Yamcha.
So why didn't you get
scared of her and run away?
It's only girls my
age that scare me.
[flames roaring]
I just can't stand this heat!
Whoa, be quiet!
If the Ox-King hears us
we're dead meat, you know?!
Boy, that sure
is a massive fire!
Well, the Dragon Ball's
definitely up in the castle,
but how do we
get it out of there?
What do you say, Goku?
Do you think you can fly up
there and get the Dragon Ball?
[GOKU] I tried that once,
and look what happened!
Goku, you're crazy!
[giggling]
I know.
Flying Nimbus!
Now you've done it!
The Ox-King heard that for sure!
Get that Dragon Ball, Goku!
Hurry back here, okay?!
[flames roaring]
[GOKU] Wow, it's hotter
than I thought up here.
Oh well, here it goes.
[GOKU screaming]
[whimpering]
[splash]
Great!
The kid's just giving up!
And we should
do the same
before we get ourselves killed!
You alright there, tail?
[BULMA squealing]
[screaming]
What're you two doing here?
Who... us? We-We
weren't doing anything?
Don't tell me you've come
to steal the treasures from
my castle, huh? Have you?!
[BULMA] Uh-uh!
I swear we didn't even know
there was a castle up there!
Right Oolong? Oolong!
[OOLONG] Uh-Huh!
Are you lying?!
[screaming]
[BULMA] Goku!
Power Pole, extend!
It looks like it's going
to be tougher than we
thought getting
into that castle.
[OX-KING] Ah-ha!
You dummy!
I knew it!
You're just stinking
treasure hunters!
[GOKU] That's not true, sir.
What do you know about truth,
you little thief?!
[BULMA] Atta boy, Goku,
keep him off balance!
[BULMA] Whoo!
[chuckling]
It's time to get serious!
Flying Nimbus!
[OX-KING] Whoa! Hey! Stop that!
[OX-KING] Cut it out!
Urgh, this guy's a rock!
Are you crazy, kid?!
Get outta there!
You can't beat the Ox-King!
You're the Ox-King??
[OX-KING] Mm-hmm.
So you're the great
Ox-King everyone's
been talking about.
No wonder you're so strong!
I know about that cloud,
and you couldn't
ride it if you stole it!
So who gave it to you?
I got it from a man who
said he was a Turtle Hermit.
Turtle Hermit?
His name's Master Roshi.
He was my old teacher! Do
you know where I can find him?
Hey, Bulma!
Do you think we could find the
place where that
Turtle Hermit lives?
The Ox-King wants to know.
Probably.
It's gotta be close to
that beach we were on.
Ooh, eee!
I can finally go
back to my castle!
Oh boy, oh boy!
Where did you get this
little toothpick that you
carry on your back, here?
Oh, that's no toothpick.
That's my Power Pole!
Cool huh? My Grandpa gave
it to me before he died.
[OX-KING] Hmm.
That's interesting.
Was his name Gohan?
[GOKU] Mm-hmm.
[OX-KING] Ah-ha!
Your grandpa Gohan
once tried to break that
toothpick on my head!
You mean you and my Grandpa
used to fight each other?
It seems our little
friend knows the Ox-King!
I can't believe it, Puar!
This kid is
starting to bug me.
Why were you and
Grandpa fighting?
[OX-KING] Because
we were like brothers!
Your grandpa was the first
pupil chosen by Master Roshi,
and I had the honor
of being the second!
Ahh, so you're Gohan's boy.
Yeah! My name is Goku!
That's a fine name!
"Goku!"
That explains why
Goku is so strong!
I should have
been nicer to him.
I hope he still wants to go
find the Dragon Balls with me.
All right, that's enough
talk about the good old days.
There's something important
I want to ask of you, Goku.
[GOKU] Yeah?
Old Master Roshi
has in his possession a
very powerful fan
made out of a palm leaf,
called the Bansho Fan.
[OX-KING] It's the only
thing that will extinguish
Fire Mountain. Will you use
the Flying Nimbus to go to him
and borrow the fan for me?
Yeah, sure.
And could you do
something for me?
Hm! Yes!
Anything you ask.
We're collecting these,
and I think you have one.
Hey!
I think I've seen
one in my castle!
Yes, of course you can
have it my new, little friend.
Aw, thanks!
[BULMA] Atta boy, Goku!
The kid saved my bacon!
I see!
So that's what those
Dragon Balls really look like!
[PUAR] I was expecting
them to be bigger.
I'll be back just
as soon as I can!
Wait! There's
something you should know!
Why, just yesterday I sent
my only daughter ChiChi
to retrieve the
Bansho Fan for me.
But now I'm worried,
'cause I feel something awful
has happened to her. Please,
Goku. Find my ChiChi, and
bring her back safely to me.
ChiChi?
Yes. She's a bit
of a coward but--Ahh...
Say Goku, how would
you like to marry her?
Uh... marry?
[snickering]
Here's a picture of ChiChi.
I'll do my best to find her.
Wow! All things considered,
she's quite a looker!
This isn't good!
Are you thinking what
I'm thinking, Yamcha?!
Yeah, I'm dead meat
if that girl's not okay!
Don't you worry Mister Ox-King,
I'll bring her back!
Good luck, son!
And be careful, Goku!
[YAMCHA] Puar, the next time
I try to smack the daughter of
some huge giant,
please, stop me!
Hey, there she is!
[PUAR] Uh-oh! She
hasn't moved a muscle!
[YAMCHA] Come on, Puar!
Hey kid! Wake up!
You can't be dead, please!
[YAMCHA] Ahh, she's
breathing Puar! She's alive!
Don't shoot, ChiChi!
I'm a friend!
Huh? How do you
know my name is ChiChi?
Uh, well let's just say
I'm a secret admirer of yours.
I didn't want to
hurt you earlier,
but you left me no choice.
Oh!
[YAMCHA] If you really want
to know the truth, my darling,
I'm in love with you. Ever since
I first set eyes on you. Truly.
Wow!
You're in love with me?
Oooh! With me?!
Of course!
I really am!
[CHICHI] Are you
telling the truth?
Just look into my face.
Can't you see it for yourself?
See?
Oh my, you look funny!
Is that, uh, tooth
gonna grow back in?
Remember the
Ox-King, Yamcha!
We don't want to
blow this little charade!
You know, you're the first boy
to say that he loves me, hehe!
Why does that not surprise me?
Oh, boy! I wonder if
papa will approve of him?
I wonder if I'm even old
enough to have a boyfriend?!
[YAMCHA] Let's get outta here!
[PUAR] Right!
Oh my!
This is all happening so fast!
I just don't
know what to think!
[crying]
What the... Hey,
I wonder where he's going?
I thought he loved me...
[CHICHI] I know! He
must be the shy type.
[CHICHI] How romantic...
Hey, are you ChiChi??
Yes I am, but I don't
think I know who you are.
You're the second
boy today who
knows my name is ChiChi.
[screaming]
[CHICHI] You must love me too!
Well, you seem like a
pretty nice person to me.
[CHICHI] But I'm not
even sure my papa will
let me have a boyfriend yet!
Well, don't worry about that,
you're dad sent me here!
I'm supposed to help
you find Master Roshi
so we can borrow the Bansho Fan!
Really? That's so sweet of you.
Well, hop on
to my Flying Nimbus,
'cause we really
should get going.
You mean,
I can actually ride on
this thing without falling?
Well, sure, but you
do have to have a pure heart.
Oh, that's okay!
When your dad's the Ox-King
you always behave well.
[grunting]
Need some help there?
Nope.
[squealing]
Well, I'm up!
Hey, what happened to you?
Well, you grabbed my
tail and I lose all my power
when somebody does that.
It's the only thing
I just can't stand!
[CHICHI] Sorry. I didn't know.
Well, it seems like
our amazing little friend
has a weak point after all.
[GOKU] Here we go!
[screaming]
Try to relax
and stand up.
Here! Take my hand!
Well, what are
you thinking Yamcha?
Should we follow them?
Don't worry about it, Puar.
He's gonna have to
come back to get the sixth
Dragon Ball from that castle.
And we'll be waiting
right here for those fools.
And after they get the
seventh ball for us,
then we'll make our move.
And I'll grab that
little monkey tail of his
with my Wolf Fang Fist!
Oh, so you are a girl!
I really wasn't sure at first.
You jerk!
[screaming]
Do you think Goku's going
to find my little ChiChi?
He'd better,
if he knows what's good for him!
Gee whiz,
you didn't have to knock me
off the cloud you know!
Well with your manners,
you'd think you
just crawled out of the woods!
[GOKU] Well I did!
[giggling]
We might never find
that Turtle Hermit out
in the middle of nowhere.
Maybe we should stop and
ask somebody for directions.
Whatever you say.
[giggling]
Uh, what are you giggling about?
Oh, about some
hunk I just met.
[GOKU] Is that all
girls ever think about?
Excuse me, can you tell me
where Master Roshi lives?
Master Roshi? Yeah!
You just keep going in that
direction and you can't
miss his little island!
Thank you! Bye-bye now!
I've never seen
a fish like that.
Wow! That must be it Goku!
I think you're right.
Let's go see.
[GOKU] Hey! Master Roshi!
[ROSHI] Hello there!
Hi.
Hop on down, kid!
I had a feeling I'd be seeing
you again some day.
Uh, this is the
great Master Roshi?
Yep. that's him.
How you doin'?
Good! For an old coot!
[NARRATOR] Our hero has found
Master Roshi, but will he be
able to fan out the
flames of Fire Mountain?
[NARRATOR] Join us next
time for Dragon Ball.