[NARRATOR] Previously on
Dragon Ball, Goku and his
new acquaintance
Krillin set out on the
Nimbus Cloud with a mission:
find a girl for Master Roshi
to date! And until the
boys complete this task,
Master Roshi won't
teach them martial arts!
[GOKU] I wonder where
we should look...?
How about not
so high in the air?
[KRILLIN screaming]
Slow down! You know
if I lose my grip on you,
I'll fall through this cloud!
Well, if you would stop
thinking bad thoughts,
then it wouldn't be a problem!
[KRILLIN] Fat chance.
Hey, Krillin, look, do you
think Master Roshi would
like that lady over there?
[KRILLIN] You mean I
have to look down?
[KRILLIN] Goku! That's a man!
[GOKU] Really?!
How can you tell?
Gosh, they all look
pretty much the same to me!
[KRILLIN] You're joking, right?
I mean you really
can't tell the difference?
Well, usually I
can figure it out.
I just have to touch them first!
In case you can't tell,
I'm a boy.
[piano music playing]
[patrons chatting]
[MAN] You sure Launch
will come here?
You just leave them
plans to me, Tall Man!
I know she's a-comin'!
[whimpering]
You think
we'll be alright?
Heard she didn't leave
a blade of cattle-grass
standin' last time!
Tubbs, you're an idiot.
The day I get bested by a
lone woman is the day I
sell my horse and go home.
Gosh! It's so dusty today
and I just washed my hair!
It ain't her.
[WOMAN] Phew, what a mess!
I don't know where I am...
Barman, I'll pay for whatever
drink the lady wants.
Huh?
[TALL MAN] Hmm. Don't
ask me why, ma'am, but,
something about you reminds
me of a girl I once loved.
[MAN 2] Listen,
partner, we're on the look out!
We don't got no time to be
flirtin' with harmless ladies!
[TALL MAN] Mind your own,
hear me?! Mind your own!
[TALL MAN] Sorry about that.
Now what can I get you?
There are so
many things I like!
How about a fresh glass
of orange juice over ice?
[BARTENDER] Comin' up!
[BARTENDER] There
you go, sweetheart!
[sniffing]
Ah... A-Achoo!
[WOMAN chuckling]
[TALL MAN] Uwaah!
[whimpering]
[WOMAN] Anyone else wanna call
me their "sweetheart"?!
[groaning]
Haven't you finished yet,
Krillin?
Hey-hey-hey!
What are you doing here?!
Go away and mind
your own business!
[GOKU] You're right,
Krillin! You are a boy.
[KRILLIN] Goku!
[train whistle blowing]
[distant train chugging]
[engine idling]
[WOMAN] It's showtime.
[brakes squealing]
[WOMAN] Thank you, sweetie!
I'll just be taking this!
That's right, Sheriff,
she derailed the train!
I am positive it was Launch!
[engine revving]
[KRILLIN] Where are
you taking us, Goku?
I doubt we'll find anyone
in the middle of the desert!
Hey, why does Master Roshi want
to meet a girl so bad anyway?
Well, I guess that he
likes going on dates just
as much as you like food!
You mean he's
going to eat her?!
[KRILLIN] No, Goku, he's not...
[police sirens]
[LAUNCH chuckling]
[POLICEMAN] Pull over, Launch,
or we're going to shoot!
[POLICEMAN] Look out!
[POLICEMAN 2] You're going to
pay for that, you vandal!
[POLICEMAN 2] How'd she do
that?!
[POLICEMAN 2] There she is!
[LAUNCH] These boys
with their pitiful aim.
[LAUNCH] Guess I'll
show 'em how it's done.
[screaming]
[LAUNCH laughing]
[sniffing]
Oh no, not now!
Ah... Ah... Achoo!
[LAUNCH] Help me!
[GOKU] Did you hear that?
I thought I heard
someone say "help"...
Then let's keep going!
"Help" only means something
dangerous is about to happen!
[GOKU] Let's find it!
Just stay where
you are, Launch!
Your crime spree
is finally over!
Move and we'll shoot!
[LAUNCH] I-I-I don't
understand...
Who are you?
E-Enough with the games, Launch!
We're police officers
and we-I mean-you
are under arrest!
[LAUNCH] Oh, that's awful!
What have I done?
Well, just about every crime
that we punish in these parts!
[POLICEMAN 3] And I assure you,
it's enough to put you away
for a long time!
[whimpering]
[screaming]
Someone help!
Huh?
Oh? It was probably
just a bird or something...
[GOKU] Hey! Right there!
But that girl's
being attacked!
Shouldn't we do something
to help her out, Krillin?
Yes, well, that would
be the heroic thing to do.
[KRILLIN] Except for, we haven't
even had our first lesson!
[KRILLIN] And they've got guns,
and handcuffs, and-
Oh, I'd say our
odds are pretty lousy...
Well in that case, we
should move in quick!
[KRILLIN] Wait!
--Oh, no!
--A monster!
What are you?!
I'm here to save that girl!
He's a kid!
I'd like to point out
that this is all his idea
and I am not involved.
I fully respect you guys.
You must be crazy if you
think I'm gonna give up
catching Launch 'coz some
child stood in my way!
Hah!
[grunting]
Scoundrel!
[GOKU] That wasn't very hard.
Oh, thank you very much!
I get so frightened
when I look at guns!
[KRILLIN] Oh, it was
nothing for us pros!
Krillin! You think that Master
Roshi would like this girl?
Huh?
Mm-hmm.
What?
We really appreciate you
coming home with us...
[LAUNCH] And where is home?
We're staying with
the Turtle Hermit!
Turtle Hermit?
[GOKU] Yup!
[GOKU] He lives on a little
island in the ocean!
[GOKU] He's kind of silly,
but we like him!
[LAUNCH] How nice!
Look, Launch!
[GOKU] There it is!
[LAUNCH] Ooh! It's a
very pretty house!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, I'm still
getting used to the pink.
Hey, Master Roshi, we're back!
There's a girl here
who wants to meet you!
How come he never
answers his door?
It is possible he's just
using the bathroom, Goku.
Why's he taking a bath?
It's the nice way
of saying "toilet"!
You mean he's taking a poo?
Oh, I'll go tell him
to hurry up, okay?
That Goku's not one
for manners, is he?
Now, Krillin, you
still haven't told me
the reason that I'm here.
Yes, well, I'm not
really sure myself.
Master Roshi is a lonely guy who
likes to think he's a stud.
So we just need someone
to play along and feed his ego.
Oh, does that mean I can hide
here while I'm running away?
Running a...? You mean from
those guys who were attacking
you and pretending to
be police officers?
So, who were they really?
They were real policemen!
U-Uh?
[GOKU] Uh, Master Roshi!
Get off the toilet!
There's a girl downstairs!
[ROSHI] Darn it, Goku!
I said hold on!
[toilet flushing]
Do you have to scream
it all over the house?!
It's plain embarrassing!
[GOKU] You're stinky!
And why exactly would
the police be after you?
I can't say for sure,
but judging from all
the money in my bag, I
probably held up a bank or two.
[ROSHI] I sure hope you brought
me a nice one this time...
[GOKU] I guess so?
Whenever Krillin sees her,
he smiles a whole lot.
Something about a train...?
[KRILLIN laughing]
Oh, right,
you're a train-robber.
You expect me to believe that?
[KRILLIN] You're so
silly, Launch.
[KRILLIN] Robbing trains
and stuff is a job for
big strong guys, and
you're a pretty girl!
[LAUNCH] You might want to
watch what you say, Krillin.
When I sneeze, I change, and
terrible things can happen!
[KRILLIN] You mean
like a runny nose?
[ROSHI] Hi!
I think I'm in love!
That's good, right?
Oh my goodness,
you frightened me!
So, Master Roshi,
what do you think of her?
She's been making up some silly
stories about robbing trains,
but other than that,
she totally fits the bill.
[ROSHI] Mm-hmm!
I'm making you both my
students from this day forward!
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Yeah!
Hey! I'm Master Roshi,
and this is my pad!
Nice to meet you, sir.
My name is Launch.
Your grandsons saved me from
a whole lot of trouble today.
Oh, is that
really true, boys?
[chuckling]
Yes, I can't thank them enough.
All in a day's work.
I'm glad you're safe, but to be
honest they're not my grandsons.
Oh.
They're my younger brothers!
[ROSHI] It was worth a try.
[laughing]
Funny joke, wasn't it?
[LAUNCH laughing]
Oh, yes!
Actually, I'm the
Turtle Hermit Master Roshi,
the world's greatest expert at
martial arts, and these boys
have come to train under me.
Martial arts, huh? Well, that
explains why Goku's so strong.
Yes, I'm happy to hear my
lessons made a difference.
But, Master Roshi, you haven't
taught me anything yet.
So, anyway, Launch, since
you're my special guest and all,
how would you like to take
a romantic walk with me
around my island paradise?
Well... it doesn't
look like a very long walk.
[LAUNCH] But yeah,
that sounds pleasant to me.
[ROSHI] Y-You mean it?! Oh boy!
[ROSHI laughing]
[KRILLIN] I think he
liked that answer.
And while you're here,
you might as well study
martial arts with us too.
I... don't know...
I have soft hands,
and I've never been
very interested in fighting.
Well, there are many benefits
of martial arts besides
being able to beat the
tar out of people, you know.
[ROSHI] It increases
your physical stamina,
it's good for the noggin',
and... it... uh, it's good
on your oily pores.
I wouldn't pass up
this opportunity, Launch!
Master Roshi is a legend
in the martial arts world!
[KRILLIN] Lots of people
would do anything for a
lesson from him.
It's like a collector's item.
Wow! Then of course I will.
Yeah... I guess there's no
point in denying my greatness.
Can we please start now?
Thanks for the plug, kid.
You know I aim to please.
[GOKU] Where's he going now?
First, let's put
our uniforms on!
Right!
[GOKU] Uniforms?
Woah, you can change in
the house, if you want!
Okay.
Yes, that's a good idea.
Now why in the world did you
have to bring that up?!
I panicked...
[ROSHI] Hurry up and
change into these!
[GOKU] Eww! I'm
not wearing that!
[ROSHI] You will if
you want lessons!
This is the only way
my plan will work!
[LAUNCH] I'm back!
This looks like underwear...
Oh, no, it's... uh....
"Turtle Hermit Fighting Armor"!
Clever name...
[LAUNCH] Okay, but it doesn't
seem to protect much...
[ROSHI] I knew these outfits
would come in handy.
Now we'll start
off with aerobics!
Would ya leave
me alone!
[sniffing]
Ah... ah...!
Oh, it's coming!
Ah... ah... ahchoo!
[LAUNCH growling]
Okay, boys, whose
idea was this?!
[LAUNCH] Wanna dress
me like a doll?!
Well, then, please
don't forget...
[LAUNCH] the accessory
machine gun!
Oh dear! S-Sorry!
You see? My other half
comes out when I sneeze,
and she doesn't like
pigheaded boys!
Did she do anything bad to you?
Not... too... bad...
[screaming]
Oh... ow!
[NARRATOR] With the mysterious
Launch moving in, maybe the boys
will learn to behave themselves.
At least, if they want to
hold on to their skin.