[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[NARRATOR] The Quarter-Finals
of the 22nd World Martial Arts
Tournament began
with Yamcha opposing Master
Shen's star pupil, Tien Shinhan.
The match quickly
turned into a battle royale
as both warriors fought
with ferocious abandon.
[NARRATOR] Seeming to
have reached a stalemate,
Yamcha called
upon his destructive
Wolf-Fang
Blowing-Wind Technique,
to which Tien responded
with fearless delight.
[NARRATOR] The crowd
had mixed reactions,
but Bulma and the others
looked on with trepidation...
While Master Shen
reveled in anticipation
of his victory over
rival, Master Roshi.
Indeed, for all those involved,
this match seemed
more like a war!
[PUAR] Block, Yamcha!
Punch him out!
[BULMA] Hit! Hit!
Hit! I said hit him!
[CROWD murmurs in shock]
How is he fighting so fast?
[CHUN thinking] Yamcha's
progress is astounding.
I'm surprised by
how much he's improved.
So what? That's it?
Your big technique?
You should rename it
Wolf-Fang-Blowing Hot Air.
Right. Let me put
it to you another way.
--[PUAR] He did it!
--[BULMA] Yamcha! Yeah!
[BULMA]
That'll show him!
What? What was that?
I'm sorry, I can't understand
you. I don't speak pain.
Gee, your concern for
your teammate is touching.
What would you do if he got
run over by a bus, yawn?
Hmmm?
[laughs]
What you lack in skill,
you more than make up
for in amusement.
Though I do think
your one-liners
are just a bit over
the top, don't you?
You want over the top?
I'll give you over the top!
Yaaaaaah!
[growls]
Hyuuuh!!
Wow, nice one.
Yes... but... not enough.
[YAMACHA] Oh...
[TIEN] Is that it?
Don't get me wrong,
I appreciate the massage...
...but I thought
you could fight.
Im... possible.
[TIEN] No...
Nothing is impossible.
Yes! Punch! Go!
[BULMA] Keep moving!
Watch out for his left!
Now hammer him! Do it!
[BULMA]
Go!!
Yamcha's in big trouble...
He's hurt.
[SHEN snickers]
[grunts]
[TIEN] For someone
who doesn't speak pain,
you sound very fluent.
You've got three eyes.
Use them and read my lips.
I'm no quitter.
I've trained too hard
to lose this match.
[YAMCHA] This one's for Nam!
Yamcha!
Oh no!
Oh, come on...
Surely you can
do better than that.
Hmph!
Come on, Yamcha!
Get up! Get up!
Oh no.
Don't give up your drive, kid.
Get up.
Surprise.
[TIEN] Hmm?
I just got my second wind...
...and it's blowing
like a hurricane.
What's Yamcha doing?
Why's he waving?
Kamehameha!
Huh?!
[CHUN thinking]
If Yamcha thinks he can handle
the Kamehameha Wave,
he must have been
hit harder than I thought.
Kame...
You're right!
How's he gonna pull that off?
Hmmm?
[YAMCHA]
...haaaaaameeeeee...
Do it... at your own risk.
...haaa!
Hyaaarrrggh!
It's coming back!
He turned it around!
On us!
[TIEN chuckles]
[screams]
Okay! How did he do that?!
Roshi's been holding out on me!
Yamcha! Look out!
[YAMCHA screams]
[BULMA sobs]
--[LAUNCH] No!
--[PUAR] Oh, Yamcha!
Hey! No fair!
[crack]
[shocked gasps and
murmurs from crowd]
Why do the psychos
always come out on my shift?
Yamcha! Yamcha! Yamcha!
Yamcha, hey! Wake up! Come on!
Hey... It doesn't take a genius
to see that he's knocked out.
Wake up.
By way of knockout,
Yamcha is unconscious and
unable to complete the fight.
Therefore, Match one is over.
The victor is Tien.
We need a doctor over here now!
Call the hospital
and get an ambulance!
Right!
Yamcha!
This wasn't supposed to happen!
I'll take him to the hospital!
[PUAR] Goku! Put him on, quick!
[GOKU] Okay. Hey, Krillin!
Help me brace his leg!
Be right there!
Hurry, Puar.
I'm going to the hospital!
Right. I'll go
with you. Come on!
This isn't over.
[GOKU] You didn't
have to break his leg...
He was already unconscious.
You did it to be mean.
[TIEN chuckles]
[TIEN] The outcome
is still the same, kid.
I won... tough break.
You may have
won the first match,
but you won't
win the tournament!
[TIEN chuckles]
Vilify me, but
that doesn't change
your friend's incompetence.
[SHEN chuckles]
Good work, Tien...
I couldn't have crushed
him better myself,
though it would
have been fun to try...
Oh, I'd love to see old
Roshi's face right about now...
The Crane flies high
while the Turtle withdraws
into his shell. Heh, heh, heh.
[CHIAOTZU] Victory.
As expected...
Though I must admit my
opponent performed much better
than I thought he would,
given his training.
[CHIAOTZU] Uh-huh.
But Yamcha was
clearly the strongest
of the three and with
him now out of the way,
there should be no trouble
in claiming the title.
'Cuz after all...
Two children are
hardly competition.
Who says success
doesn't come easy, huh?
[SPONSOR] We hope you've
all enjoyed today's match
and invite you to
return with us tomorrow
as defending champion
Jackie Chun faces off
against the ferocious
Big Bad Man Wolf.
It's a fight you won't want
to miss, kids, so arrive early!
[GOKU] Tomorrow's
your day big day.
Are you nervous?
Mhmm. I wouldn't
be here if I wasn't.
Every day brings
new challenges
and not all of them
are confined to a ring.
[growling and howling]
Uh...
[growling]
[CHUN] Nice pipes, kid, but
you're drooling on your chin.
I know!
He definitely has issues
and they all seem
to be directed at you.
Huuuuh?
I know I let you down.
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
You didn't let anyone down.
You did your best.
Everybody knows that.
That's all that counts.
[KRILLIN] Anyway, it's not
you who should be ashamed.
It's that dirty, rotten Tien!
[GOKU] Yamcha!
Don't worry about him.
I'll make sure he
learns his lesson.
No. No, Goku!
It's not worth it.
That Tien is a ruthless man.
Heh!
I know.
Yamcha... You've had a long day.
It's time you got some rest.
Yeah...
Goku, fight!
Don't let him win the title.
Right.
Goku, don't focus all your
energy on one adversary.
There are plenty
of matches to be fought
before you have the
chance to take on Tien.
Concentrate on the now.
I'll try, Master.
[approaching footsteps]
Hmm?
Huh?
[GOKU] Hmm?
Hmph.
[grunts]
[growls]
Bring us the best
you have to offer.
We're here tonight to
celebrate the flawless victory
of my star pupil, Tien!
Yes.
Tell us, how does
it feel, Tien,
[laughs] knowing you decimated
Turtle's prime fighter?
Crushing Yamcha was as
easy as clenching my fist.
It was no real challenge.
[chortles]
He was a coward.
He was completely unprepared.
Nyahahahaha!
[GOKU] Stop laughing!
Huh?
At least Yamcha is honest.
[ROSHI] Goku, this
isn't the time to fight.
[BULMA]
Please don't make a scene.
I'll go wash my hands.
Enjoy.
Tien... Eat hardy...
Your technique
today was flawless...
...unlike some competitors.
[ROSHI growls]
[ROSHI] If you have something
to say, say it to my face.
Pyew! I can't stand
the stench of loser!
Waitress, please! I demand
another table at once!
[spitting]
You foul nuisance!
Why don't you get a real hat?!
Got one, thanks!
That one squawks!
Hey! What's that on the floor?
Did you lose another tooth?!
[ROSHI] At least mine are real!
[SHEN] They're real,
alright, real ugly!
[ROSHI] Oh, nice one!
Where did you get that joke?
Out of your stupid hat?
[NARRATOR] The sun shines
on a new morning
as preparations begin
for today's competition.
[NARRATOR] In a short while,
the deserted square will
be bustling with competitors
and eager patrons
roaring with excitement
over the anticipated
mayhem of Match Two.
[JUDGE A] I don't know, I think
the orange looks fine, actually.
Cecil, what
are you talking about?
Look at us, it's like
we're in road construction!
[GOKU] Hey, Mr. Chun!
[KRILLIN] Are you ready
for your big fight?
[CHUN] Ready as I'll ever be.
[GOKU] I think
you'll win, Mr. Chun.
[CHUN] Jackie.
[growling]
[KRILLIN and GOKU]
Uh...
[NARRATOR] Competitive
spirit is one thing,
but Man Wolf seems
down right ferocious.
What is the cause of his
distaste for Jackie Chun?
And which team
will win the title?
Crane? Turtle?
Or possibly neither?
[NARRATOR] The answers
to these conundrums
and many more lie ahead
on the next thrilling
episode of Dragon Ball!