[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Goku faced off in a fierce match
with a mysterious
masked competitor.
It was a close bout
complete with a double dose
of destructive Kamehameha waves!
The fight took
an unexpected turn
when the anonymous combatant
latched onto Goku's tail
and broke it right off!
But the real shocker
came with the unmasking
of the mystery fighter...
The masked man was none other
than Goku's beloved
grandfather, Gohan!
But Gohan's pass
from Other World
was soon to expire,
and so the reunion
was woefully short
for Goku and his grandfather.
As they said their goodbyes,
Baba the fortuneteller
used her mystical skills
to locate the final Dragon Ball.
Now only a lone car
and its unknown occupants
stand in Goku's way!
So I suppose this means
you're taking off
after that car now?
[GOKU] You bet I am!
Yeah!
It shouldn't take
too long to find it.
I'll be back soon with all
seven of the Dragon Balls!
Hold on. It's not
going to be that easy.
There's got to be
dozens of cars
that look just like that one.
Is that all
you're worried about?
There's not much
traffic out there.
Finding the car will be
the least of your problems.
Wait, if the ball
is just in some car,
why couldn't we
pick it up on the radar?
Ugh! Don't tell me...
...this thing is
on the fritz again!
[GOKU] Well, whatever.
I'm gonna go now.
So I should go
that direction, right?
[BABA]
Mmm-hmm.
Hello? Hey, Flying Nimbus!
I'm going to leave the other
Dragon Balls with you, Upa.
Put 'em in a safe place!
[UPA] I will.
This is so cool!
We're going to see all seven
Dragon Balls come together!
[UPA thinking]
Yeah, but the very best part
is that my Dad is coming back.
[GOKU] Let's go, flying Nimbus!
We'll be waiting!
Hurry!
I wonder who's in that car.
And how did they hide the
Dragon Ball from us like that?
[PILAF] So that's
the whole plan. Got it?
--Sure!
--Yes!
It's just brilliant, sire!
[chuckles]
I know your little secret, kid.
You've got quite a weak spot.
His tail...
The boy is lucky I just now
found out about this one,
know what I mean?
I could've crushed him long ago.
But the time has come,
Monkey Boy.
Finally, my time has come!
I know!
We've been chasing after this
kid a long time, haven't we?
It feels like a lifetime.
No, make that two lifetimes!
[APE GOKU roaring]
[screaming]
[roars]
[SHU and MAI coughing]
I put you guys through
a lot, didn't I?
Oh... it was... my pleasure.
But still, it's been
tough for us all.
But, oh, we will
have our revenge!
Welcome to the Pilaf Dynasty!
--I... rule!
--[rooster crowing]
So tell us, sire.
What'll you do
with all that power?
Let's see...
First of all... um, well...
it's complicated.
What? You just gotta
let us in on it!
Well... I thought...
Come on!
The suspense is killing me!
Okay...
There must be something...
Spill it!
Butt out! It's my
world domination plan!
There! That wasn't
too hard to find!
Wh-Wh-What... was that noise?
Um... A rock, maybe?
Or a bird?
Hi there!
Have you found a Dragon Ball?
Hey, do... do I know you?
Haven't I seen you
around some place?
[screaming]
[tires squealing,
GOKU yells]
Isn't he that kid?
Again? Doesn't he ever quit?
How did he find us?
Hmmm...
I know I've seen
that blue guy before.
I thought this safe
was supposed to hide
the Dragon Ball from his radar!
You just can't get a
quality product these days!
Hey! Now I remember you!
I fought with you before.
You're bad people!
You tried to hurt me
and my friends!
Well, change of plans.
We could go ahead and
clobber him, but, uh...
Our surprise attack is shot.
No problem!
Don't you worry.
This little snag could be a
golden opportunity for us, Mai.
We do have him alone out here
in the middle of
nowhere, after all...
Come, here my jewel.
This is it.
We'll take care of him
right here, right now.
[GOKU] Hey! Get out of there!
[GOKU] I wonder why they
look so happy to see me?
So... we meet once again.
Or should I say one last time.
[GOKU]
I know you only want to get
all the Dragon Balls
to make some awful wish.
But I have something really
important to do with that ball,
so hand it over!
[PILAF laughing]
[PILAF] What?
Do you think you have
some puny little dream
that's worthier than
my imperial ambitions?
Maybe we should
flip a coin for it.
Wait, I have an idea.
Why don't we have an old
fashioned showdown right here?
Winner take all?
If you beat us, I'll personally
hand over this Dragon Ball.
But if you happen to lose,
we get the six you already
have in your possession.
How did you know
I already collected
six of the Dragon Balls?
[laughing]
Life is quite a
mystery, isn't it?
Well, boy, what d'ya say?
Should we shake on it?
Do we have ourselves a deal?
Sure thing!
Let's get this thing over with.
I'm in a hurry.
Okay. It's set.
Pinky swear on it!
Hey! It's impolite to swear!
You uncivilized idiot!
You've never heard of
pinky swearing before?
It's like a handshake,
but instead of holding hands,
you link your
little fingers together.
Next, you shake it up
and down like this
and now the deal is sealed!
[laughs proudly]
Now... that was a promise.
You can't take it back!
Then let's do this!
[PILAF] Hmm. You seem
pretty sure of yourself.
Well don't count
us out just yet!
Get a load of this!
--[SHU] Let's go!
--[MAI] Hurry!
Wait... hey, wait!
[PILAF] I need a boost!
[PILAF, SHU, MAI laughing]
What in... the world...?
[PILAF] Ta-da!
We just wanted to slip into
something more comfortable.
These are the most advanced
armored battle pods ever made!
I call them my Power Suits!
Wow...
[PILAF] Are you ready
to give yourself up?
You are obviously no match
for my metallic marvels!
No way! We haven't even started!
Well, well. You don't
scare easily, do you?
I'll never be scared of you!
Never say never, nitwit!
You're so primitive!
Don't you recognize
a fine piece of machinery
when you see it?
You didn't even ask
to see under the hood.
Well, I'll show you
all the features anyway.
Just yell if you
have any questions!
You think it's so strong,
then prove it!
[growls]
Brat!
Mai, the boy wants some proof.
What d'ya say you give him
a little demonstration?
Uh... Why do I have to do it?
It's your privilege to
go first. You're the boss!
You don't trust my invention?
Are you saying you doubt
my technological savvy?
No, of course not, Emperor.
Mai! Is that fear
I see in your eyes?
[MAI] No.
Hey!
If none of you are going to
go first, then I guess I will!
[yells]
[PILAF, SHU, MAI yelling]
[GOKU grunts]
He's down...
[laughing]
You fell down and went boom!
Hey...
[PILAF laughs]
[SHU] Good work, Sire!
[MAI] Bravo, Emperor! Bravo!
[screams]
[PILAF laughs]
[PILAF] That will never work!
This baby's made of triple
reinforced titanium!
It's a hundred times stronger
than regular steel!
Wow! Sounds like that
stuff is really strong.
That's what I said.
[GOKU yelling]
Take this!
[PILAF laughing]
[MAI] Excellent move!
[KRILLIN] I didn't think Goku
would be gone this long.
I still think that
was strange. Don't you?
[YAMCHA] What's strange?
The car!
Don't you think
it was a little weird
that the ball
wasn't on our radar?
I'm sure he's fine!
Oh, yeah, Goku
can handle himself.
You should just try
to sit back and relax.
Baba! You can help me!
Do you think you
could take another look
in your crystal ball and tell me
who was driving the car?
Give me ten million Zeni.
What?! Look, we already
won your stupid tournament!
Why do we have to pay you?
That was a one-time only deal.
Why you...
Don't you have
enough money already?
Can't you do this one thing?!
[BABA blows raspberry]
She's still as stingy
and stubborn as ever!
No... That was just a joke!
I meant that you're still as
pretty and as charming as ever!
[KRILLIN]
How'd that crow get in here?
That's a bad omen!
You mean a bad omen about Goku?
Get out of here! Shoo! Go on!
Oh, bad luck!
[BABA] More bad luck?!
[UPA thinking]
Please, no! Not Goku!
Ow, my head!
Can you believe this guy?
He's so hard headed!
Go on, Shu.
Now bury him for good!
[SHU] Yes, Sire!
[PILAF]
That's some sharp shooting, Shu!
Power Pole extend!
[GOKU]
Yah!
Emperor!
[SHU] Are you okay, Master?
[MAI] Don't try to move, Sire!
[GOKU] Do you give up now?
[PILAF]
No! We will never surrender!
No more fooling around!
[PILAF thinking]
All right, it's no big deal...
I just have to get a hold
of his tail, that's all.
I can do it!
[growling]
Shu, Mai. Listen up!
We're back to the original plan!
[BOTH] Yes sire!
[GOKU] What are you doing?
Okay! We'll go on my count!
One... two...
Wait! Hang on a second, Emperor!
What's the problem now?!
[SHU]
I don't see his tail anywhere!
Maybe he's got it stuck
inside his pants or something!
What! Let me think...
Uhh... Give me a minute.
Let's discuss this!
If you'll excuse us
for just a moment...
Hey! Come on!
[SHU]
So what do we do now, Emperor?
[MAI] What about this?
[muffled whispers]
[PILAF]
That sounds like it'd work...
[GOKU] Hurry up over there!
[PILAF]
Break! Sorry for the wait!
We ran into a little glitch,
but we can proceed
with your destruction now!
We'll see about that! Let's go!
Now!
[PILAF]
Everyone hold your positions!
Look!
Do it now, Shu!
[GOKU] Let me go!
[PILAF laughing]
[PILAF] We should be able
to find his tail now!
This won't hurt a bit!
[GOKU] I've got to get
this thing off of me!
[MAI] Sire! Hurry!
I can't hold on much longer!
Grab his tail!
What's going on? Grab his tail!
What's the problem?!
Emperor Pilaf!
Is there something wrong?
He... has no tail...
It's gone... His tail's gone...
Why'd you have to
go and do that?
This is the only outfit
I brought here with me!
[MAI, SHU, PILAF]
What happened to your tail?!
[GOKU]
My tail? It got pulled off!
What are we supposed
to do now, Emperor?
[PILAF] We still have our armor!
He's got to tire out sometime!!
Now let's finish this!
It's taken long enough!
[PILAF] Okay, you two!
Get connected!
[GOKU]
Whoa!
[PILAF] Pretty handy, huh?
So you throwing in
the towel now, Shorty?
Ka-me-ha-me...
--[SHU] Huh?
--[MAI] Hmm?
[PILAF]
What's he saying down there?
[GOKU] ...ha!
And that was not
even at my full power!
Well, he's possessed.
That explains it...
Sir, the second unit
is not responding!
It's completely destroyed!
So?
Ditch it and transform the
others into the emu module!
[MAI] Yes, sir!
What can a big bird do?
Run.
[PILAF] See ya, sucker!
You won't get away
from me that easy!
He's right on our heels!
Doesn't this thing
go any faster?
Just launch the missile!
[SHU] Fire in the hole!
[PILAF] Mom?
Can I please have your
Dragon Ball now, mister?
Take it...
[PILAF] Please take it...
One more thing...
[SHU] Huh? Oh...
Thank you! It's a perfect fit!
This will be our little secret.
[GOKU] Good bye!
Good...
--...bye.
--Bye...
Where are we going
to go now, Emperor?
Well I sure
don't think we should
follow the Dragon Balls anymore.
Shut up!
[NARRATOR]
Goku has finally collected
all seven Dragon Balls!
In no time, he'll be helping
his broken-hearted friend
Upa get an incredible wish!
I got it, Upa!
I'll be there real soon!
[NARRATOR] You don't want
to miss the next episode,
when the Eternal Dragon appears,
on Dragon Ball!