[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[BULMA]
You can't be!
No way!
Goku?
[NARRATOR] Three years
have passed since Goku
and his friends
parted company to embark
on their separate training.
The cheerful reunion didn't
last long as a storm blew in.
[BOY yells]
[NARRATOR] The raging
storm brought with it
King Piccolo's
alter ego, Junior.
His arrival offered
little surprise to Goku,
who agreed to face
Piccolo's offsrping
in exchange for the
resurrection of his friends,
Krillin, Chiaotzu,
and Master Roshi.
And now, the World Martial
Arts Tournament begins!
[birds chirping]
[distant chatter]
[eerie music plays]
[TIEN gasps]
I... I don't believe it!
[GOKU] He arrived
just like I expected.
[CONTESTANTS chatter]
[TIEN]
Uh! Goku, is it possible...
...one of Piccolo's
henchmen survived?
Yeah, in a manner of speaking.
I was afraid of that!
I wouldn't tell the others
about this, if I were you.
If they found out,
it would just upset them
and start trouble.
[KRILLIN]
Goku, who was that guy?
Do you know him from somewhere?
He seemed to know you.
Was he giving you trouble?
Well, uh, we were just
talking about that.
Uh, he looked pretty strong,
didn't he, Tien?
[TIEN]
Mmm.
[CHIAOTZU] Tien, that
looked like King Piccolo.
[TIEN]
Don't say anything.
[CHIAOTZU]
Uh, okay.
[KRILLIN, YAMCHA]
Huh?
[TIEN] I will respect
Goku's wishes, for now.
Hm?
Uh, huh?
[KRILLIN, TIEN]
Uh?
[romantic tune plays]
Hi, Goku.
[BOTH] Aaaah...
[WOMAN giggles]
Hm. Uh, do I know you?
[gasps, yells]
You fool!
[grunting]
Are you okay?
Was it something I said?
[WOMAN grunts]
[GOKU]
She's a very strange girl.
What a dream!
Strange as in wonderful.
She's so beautiful!
Wow, who is she?
Come on, Goku. We're your pals.
You can tell us.
I don't have a clue! I've never
met her before in my life.
Stop it! Do you
expect us to believe
that she yelled at you
for no reason?
I don't know her, honest.
Was she a part of your
difficult training?
Just what have you been up
to for the past three years?
Goku! Training for a tournament
isn't a game, you know!
Didn't you learn
the word "discipline"?!
[grumbling]
That girl definitely
knew Goku from somewhere,
wouldn't you agree, Tien?
Uh, yes.
[RECEPTIONIST]
Attention participants.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
We will now begin
the preliminary round.
Please gather at
the center of the room.
[COMMISSIONER]
I'd like to thank all of you
for your support of
the Martial Arts Society.
As you know, the World
Martial Arts Tournament
is held once every three years.
This year, the number
of participants is 72,
much lower than the record
numbers enjoyed last time.
Unfortunately, recent events
have thinned our roster.
I am also aware
that the difficult
and dangerous reputation
carried by this event
may have scared many
would-be participants away.
Therefore, it is safe to say
that the 72 warriors
who stand before me
are of the highest caliber.
[TIEN]
It doesn't make sense.
Why would Piccolo's underling
show up at the tournament?
Why now?
[yelps]
[CROWD cheering]
[ROSHI]
Look at this crowd!
[BULMA] I think we're gonna
be stuck here a while.
It's a sea of people.
What are you complaining about,
you furry balloon?
[BULMA groans]
Hey! Wait a minute!
Ease up! Stop pushing!
Oh! It's okay!
Keep pushing! Mm.
Why don't you watch
where you're going, pal!
[ROSHI groans]
Why do you always have
to get us in trouble?
It wasn't on purpose.
[announcement tune chimes]
[ANNOUNCER] It is time
for the lottery.
Participants will be paired
according to the numbers drawn.
Oh, I hope the boys won't
have to fight one another
during the preliminary round.
There's nothing
we can do about it.
[PUAR]
I'll go find out.
Puar, you can't get in.
It's authorized personnel only.
Birds can go anywhere!
That's a good idea!
[TIEN] Chiaotzu,
disperse the numbers so that
we don't have to
fight each other.
[CHIAOTZU]
Mhm.
[TIEN] And place Piccolo's
lackey in a different block.
I want to see
how he fights first.
[CHIAOTZU]
Okay.
[GOKU]
Hm.
I'm number two.
Looks like I'll be
in the first match of block one.
I'm in block two.
How about you, Krillin?
The last half of block one.
I'll be in the
last half of block two.
Oh, wow! Chiaotzu
isn't going to fight until...
...the last half
of block three.
This is great! None of us
have to fight each other.
Amazing!
[KRILLIN]
What a coincidence!
[CHIAOTZU giggles]
Which block is he in?
I wonder which block she's in?
Huh.
So, where did you guys end up?
What happened?
Well, we won't have to
fight against one another,
at least not until the finals.
Perfect! Better than
you hoped for!
[YAMCHA]
Mhm!
[OOLONG]
Good luck, Goku.
Thanks.
[ANNOUNCER] The preliminaries
are about to begin.
Of the 72 competitors, only 8
will advance to the next round.
First up will be
the matches in block one.
Remember the rules of conduct.
If you fall off
the stage, pass out,
or surrender, you lose.
Kills are not permitted
in this event.
Violators will be expelled,
no exceptions.
Be careful. Fight well.
At this time, number 2 and 3
please come up to the stage.
That's me.
All right, Goku.
Let's just see if all your
training really paid off.
[GOKU laughs]
Well, I know he's improved.
The real question is how much.
[KRILLIN chuckles] I think
we're in for a good show!
[gasps]
[GOKU] Chapa! But I heard
you were destroyed
by Piccolo's enforcer.
King Chapa. Goku has it tough.
I have fought the one called
Tambourine and survived.
Hm. Goku...
I have waited a long time
to get back in
the ring with you.
You and I have some
unfinished business.
Long before your lucky victory
during our last encounter,
I was champion
of this tournament.
Now I will have my revenge.
Did you get your
complimentary T-shirt?
You can have it
embroidered for five zeni.
I don't ever wear shirts.
They chafe my skin.
Well, you're missing out.
Yeah, well they used
to give away posters.
I got mine signed by Chapa
the year he was champion.
I will reclaim the title.
You don't stand a chance, Goku.
Ready! You may now begin!
[CHAPA groans]
[yells]
I have developed
a few new moves, Goku.
Just for this occasion.
[CHAPA groans]
It that your defense?
You fool.
Are you so weak that
you won't even try to fight?
[CHAPA grunts]
[OOLONG] I don't get it.
Why is he just standing there?
[YAMCHA]
Don't worry. He's okay.
I can't sense anything from him.
His mind is completely cleared.
If King Chapa doesn't realize
it, he won't stand a chance.
Focus... Win.
[gasping]
[yells]
[grunting]
Where has he gone?
Stop hiding!
Do you hear me, you coward?!
[groans]
[CROWD gasp, murmur]
Uhhh...
Number 3 has fainted.
Number 2 is the winner!
[CROWD cheering]
[MAN]
Incredible!
I'm glad I got to see it
from the front row!
That's fantastic! Puar,
let's go tell the others!
I have a feeling we haven't
begun to see Goku's power.
Yes.
Look. He doesn't even blink.
[CROWD cheering]
[JUNIOR] How easily
the crowd is entertained.
Goku hasn't begun to
unleash his full power.
[scoffs]
However, with moves
that elementary,
he hardly stands a chance.
I'll rip him into pieces
in front of his friends.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
Hm? Really? Sounds like
Goku has improved.
He had Chapa going...
[grunting]
He went down fast!
I'm not surprised. Goku's hard
training is starting to pay off.
Yamcha's been training
just as hard.
They all have.
I wonder how it's going?
[OOLONG] Time to
sprout wings again.
[CROWD cheering]
[BOTH grunting]
Hm!
[OPPONENT C groans]
[YAMCHA yells]
[OPPONENT D yelps]
[giggles]
Huh.
[yells]
[CHIAOTZU yells]
--[CROWD gasping]
--[ALL] Hm?
Aah! Chiaotzu!
Chiaotzu!
[grunting]
[GOKU]
Is he okay?
How could this
have happened? Chiaotzu!
Wake up.
[MAN chuckles]
I didn't kill him,
though he should have died.
However, I didn't
want to be expelled.
You will pay for this!
Aah!
We meet again, Shinhan.
No! You're dead!
Not quite.
And you must be Goku.
Uh. That's right. How do you
know my name? Who are you?
Aah!
Aah! Mercenary Tao!
[chuckles]
That's right.
Like my new look?
But... Mercenary Tao died.
How is this possible?
[TAO] With a good imagination
and a lot of zeni.
There is life after death,
but it's not cheap.
It took a while for me
to get my parts in order,
but here I am.
The world's first
fully-functioning
cyborg assassin.
Uh, excuse me.
I'm sorry, but you'll
have to leave the stage.
The next match
is about to commence.
Hmm...
You seem to enjoy your life.
It would be a shame
if I had to take it away.
Stay!
Goku, a little
background would help.
He's Mercenary Tao, a killer.
Killer?
He's also the younger brother
of Shen, the Crane Hermit.
[gasps]
And if I understand
their order correctly,
that makes him Tien
and Chiaotzu's superior.
How do you know this guy?
He tried to kill my
friends and I stopped him.
[TAO groans]
Accept this apology!
[GOKU yells]
[yells]
There was a big explosion,
and then he was gone.
That's right. And little
Goku was responsible
for that big explosion.
After that, you could say
my entire life fell to pieces.
What now?
That's up to Goku.
I'm here to fight, but it's
not the title I'm after.
[GOKU]
Then what do you want?
Revenge. An eye for an eye,
if you get my meaning.
I can take your life now,
or crush you in the ring.
After that, I will deal
with you, Tien Shinhan.
Once my brother's star pupil,
now a--what's the word?
Mmm. A traitor.
I did not betray Master Shen.
I was loyal to his house.
Until...
I discovered I did not
share his ideals.
[TAO chuckles]
Your fate has been sealed.
Then so be it. I will
fight you for Chiaotzu.
[laughing]
You haven't changed.
You still have a big mouth.
I'll gladly shut it.
[NARRATOR]
Mercenary Tao, the world's
most notorious assassin,
has returned from the grave
to seek revenge.
His mechanical sights are
set on Goku and his friends.
Will they find the strength
to thwart this lethal menace?
He's already defeated
Chiaotzu! Who's next?
There's only one way
to find out.
Stay tuned for the next
action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball!