[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
King Piccolo launched an
attack on the Eastern City,
laying it to waste,
and declaring himself
ruler of the sector.
[BOTH yell]
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Tien Shinhan,
consumed with his desire
to destroy King Piccolo,
mastered the
Evil Containment Wave.
[TIEN]
I've done it.
[NARRATOR] Goku downed the
dangerous Ultra Divine Water
in hopes of increasing
his abilities.
The gamble paid off,
as he was rewarded
with mysteriously
strengthened powers.
[roars]
I don't know. I feel different,
but I just can't explain it.
[NARRATOR] King Piccolo
began his reign of terror
with a nationally
televised announcement
of horrific proportions.
My first decree is
to abolish the police
and release all criminals!
I want riots!
Order is legally dead!
[NARRATOR] As a result of
Piccolo's savage policies,
pandemonium erupted
in the streets as reason
gave way to unbridled chaos.
[BOTH chuckle]
[hollering]
[PUAR] Guys, come in here!
It's another news bulletin.
[PICCOLO] Good afternoon,
my loyal citizens.
I have more news
of terror and mayhem!
As members of my new order,
you should all prepare
for destruction.
Lousy monster!
Who does he think he is?!
Get ready as I unleash the most
glorious terror imaginable!
Is he serious?!
[PICCOLO]
No need to worry, however.
I've taken care of
all the arrangements.
I know that all of you
share my enthusiasm.
Because, it is
a privilege and honor
to be a part of this event.
You're gonna love this!
[PICCOLO]
Your planet, heh, my planet,
is divided into 43 sectors.
Each is represented
by a slip of paper
which has been
placed in this box.
To commemorate the
anniversary of my rule,
I declare this day,
May 13th, as Piccolo Day.
As part of this
annual celebration,
I'll draw a slip
from the box each year.
And guess what folks.
There's more.
[chuckles]
[BOTH whimper]
The chosen sector will
host that year's celebration,
which will culminate
in its destruction.
And I will do the honors.
No! You wouldn't!
I am not without mercy.
The sector's annihilation
will be instantaneous.
There will hardly
be time to feel any pain.
That's horrific! Why would
you do something so cruel?!
Hm! It's nothing new.
This world celebrates
occasions with
explosions in the sky.
Mine are just a
little more dangerous.
Besides, I can't wait to see
the terror on peoples' faces.
And after all,
it is my celebration.
[laughs]
That maniac!
He's an A-1 sicko.
Please, don't worry. This is
meant to be happy fun time.
The drawing will only
be held once a year.
That means,
if you're lucky,
some of you may live
another 43 years.
[laughs]
Or not!
43 years?! Oh, how generous!
I'd rather be destroyed now than
have to live my life in fear!
[PICCOLO] But seriously,
I wish to maintain
an open dialogue
with my subjects.
So, if for any reason
you are displeased
with my plan
or any of my policies,
please feel free
to pay me a visit.
My door is always open.
Tell me what's on your tiny
little minds. I'm here for you.
And once you've unloaded
all your emotional baggage,
I promise to remove your
troubles, permanently.
[laughs]
Daddy! I'm so scared.
Please say you'll defeat him.
Please say you'll save me from
that mean old King Piccolo!
Uh, well, you see ChiChi,
uh, Daddy wants to
defeat that monster, but it's
impossible, mmm sweetheart.
But Daddy, is he really
stronger than you?
Afraid so, Muffinhead.
No one of this world
can defeat that beast.
Uh, what about...
Goku! That's it!
Goku can defeat him,
right Daddy? Right?
No. No way.
Not even Goku. Sorry.
Yes he can, Dad. Goku will
defeat King Piccolo! I know it!
Now Goku can beat Piccolo.
Don't you think?
[KORIN]
I don't know.
See, the outcome
rests in the hands of fate.
Goku has the necessary skills.
However,
that's not always enough.
That doesn't fill me
with confidence.
Anyway, at a time like this,
I'd rather be filled with food.
I'm gonna stuff my belly with
everything I can fit into it!
Go for it. Have as many
Senzu Beans as you want.
I don't want beans
at a time like this!
I'm a gourmet at heart.
I want something special!
Oh!
It's time for a road trip.
I'll find something
really tasty!
Do you mind if I borrow your
Nimbus Cloud for a while?
Like I said before,
the Nimbus Cloud
will do you no good, Yajirobe.
You have to be
pure heart to ride it.
Heh. I'll tell you something.
My heart is as pure
as the blue skies.
[KORIN]
Hm!
Watch me!
[yelling]
[KORIN] More like a pure bowl
of pudding. Have a nice trip!
[YAJIROBE yelling]
Uah!
[grunts]
Here!
[giggles]
[YAJIROBE yells]
Ah...
[YAJIROBE]
Uh! Aah...!
[BORA]
Huh?
Papa, isn't that...?
--[UPA] Yajirobe!
--[YAJIROBE] Mm?
Uh! What happened to Goku?
Is he all right?!
[YAJIROBE]
Easy, easy.
Your friend is fine
as far as I know.
He's gone now though.
Oh.
Please be careful.
Goku.
[PICCOLO] I must confess
I'm not long on patience.
Why wait for tomorrow when
I can have fun right now?
Today I will
draw the first lot.
Not so fast, monster!
The Evil Containment Wave
will have you soon!
[KING FURRY grunts]
[PICCOLO laughs]
Let's see. Who will
be the first to go?
Hm. Let's see...
[chatter, gasping]
Oh, not too far away.
Heh. Looks like sector 28!
Your time is up!
Ha! Get ready. I'll be
visiting you very soon.
Uh! Oh no!
Please, not sector 28!
That's West City. It's where
my parents are living!
[MRS. BRIEF]
Oh, thank goodness!
At least Bulma
doesn't live there.
My little pumpkin will be safe.
I feel sorry for those
that live in West City.
Wait a minute. West City?
That's where we live.
We should invite her over
for brunch this week.
It's been too long since
we last saw our little--
This is Kame House calling
Tien Shinhan, come in!
Tien Shinhan! Do you read me?!
Please keep King Piccolo
from going to the West City!
That's where my parents live!
[BULMA grunts]
[TIEN]
Ugh... Don't worry.
Piccolo's reign is over!
[car horns honking]
--[PEOPLE yelling]
--[car horns honking]
[sobbing]
[PEOPLE yelling]
[CHILD]
Aah!
[tires screech]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[MAN]
Do you call that driving?!
[BEAR] You're the one
who ran into me!
[car horn honks]
--[PEOPLE yelling]
--[car horns honking]
[distant sirens]
[PEOPLE yelling]
Hey! What are you doing?!
Can't you make
that thing go any faster?!
Look, you idiot! This is a bus!
I'm not the one who's drivin'!
[distant dogs barking]
Meow!
[dogs barking,
cats meowing]
Sweetheart, what are you doing?
We've got to get out of here.
Traffic's going to be terrible.
Just a minute, Honey.
I can't find Scratch.
Oh Scratch! Hm.
[SCRATCH meows]
Scratchy?!
--[MRS. BRIEF] Uh...
--[SCRATCH meows]
[MRS. BRIEF]
Where is that cat?
[sighs]
--[SCRACH] Meow!
--[MRS. BRIEF] Uh!
Meow, meow!
There's Momma's baby.
Here Scratch!
--[SCRACTH meows]
--[MRS. BRIEF giggles]
Promise you won't scare
Momma like that again.
Meow.
Scratch, that's all
you think about.
Uh! Well, excuse me!
I wasn't gonna
leave her behind.
Are you sure
you have everything?
Mmm!
[laughs]
The plants! I forgot!
[gasps]
I completely forgot to
water them this morning.
Darling, you know how upset
the chrysanthemums get
when they go without
their morning sprinkle.
Thank you, Sweetheart,
for reminding me
of the important things in life.
Thank Scratch.
Meow.
[NEWSCASTER]
Again, riots and pandemonium
have beset the streets of this
once tranquil West City.
This was the scene
only moments ago.
[PEOPLE screaming]
It's insane out there.
Please let my parents
be all right.
[ALL gasp]
Who are you
and what do you want?!
[CONVICTS chuckle]
[CONVICT A clears throat]
We want your food.
And your zeni. All of it.
And what if we
don't feel like donating?
Too bad. Just consider us the
jail break collection agency.
Jail breakers!
You got it!
We didn't escape. We were
liberated by King Piccolo.
We're under his orders.
We're legit!
The criminals are now the
heroes, thanks to Piccolo!
That's right. All the prisons
across the entire country
have been abolished.
[whimpers]
Now, give us all
your food and zeni or else.
[OOLONG, BULMA screaming]
[BOTH chuckle]
Come on, Blue!
Go get us something to eat.
And nothing instant.
Uh! All you'll get from me
is a knuckle sandwich!
[CONVICT C groans]
This one's feisty!
[laughs]
I'll just cook you...
medium well.
--[BULMA] Yamcha!
--[YAMCHA yells, grunts]
[CONVICT C groans]
So long!
[LAUNCH]
Yamcha!
[grunts]
Heh-heh!
[YAMCHA groans]
Oh! This is the
end of the world.
Everything's spun outta control.
Goku, Master Roshi,
Chiaotzu, Krillin.
Everybody's gone.
Even Tien Shinhan.
I know my leg's not
completely healed yet,
but I have to do something.
I can't just wait around!
[GOKU]
I'm coming, Piccolo!
The end is near, Piccolo!
[PIANO] The seaplane
is ready, your Majesty.
[PICCOLO] Perfect! I can't
wait to hear their screams!
West City will fall, and I will
enjoy every last minute of it!
[chuckles]
There it is! King's Castle.
I hope I'm not too late.
[PICCOLO] Not very spacious,
but I love the décor.
[chuckles]
I see you, Monster!
Oh good, a guest.
Why don't you come down
from your fortress, Piccolo?!
I've got something to give you!
Heh. How very thoughtful of you.
Did you pick it out yourself?
This world certainly has
a bountiful supply
of idiots, sire.
Quite true,
but they're so amusing.
Even so, we can't have
upstarts running amuck.
I'll make an example
of this one.
A live broadcast of this
destruction should do the trick.
Yes sire.
[laughs intensely]
Almost there. Come on Nimbus,
let's go faster!
[TIEN] Let's go Piccolo.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid of me?
Why are you in
such a hurry to die?
Come on, now.
You're not the only one
I have to destroy today.
That's it, stay smug.
Catching you off guard'll
make my job that much easier.
Hope you like your new throne.
An electric jar!
[TIEN bellows]
[grunts, yells]
[grunting]
[yells]
Oh, let's go! I've got
a schedule to keep!
I'm late for an extermination.
[TIEN]
Hmm.
Oh, you do that
almost as well as I.
Looks like someone's
been practicing.
[TIEN] I have to find
a way to get closer to him.
You must take great
pride in your abilities.
Though it will take much more
than a fancy landing
to defeat me, boy.
For once, I agree
with you, creature.
I've come prepared!
[grunts]
That's the problem
with the human race,
no respect for
the superior species.
Superior? Don't make me laugh.
I'm surprised
you can walk upright.
[TIEN] A little closer.
Five more feet and I'll be able
to use the
Evil Containment Wave!
Ha! The only thing big
about you is your mouth.
You're nothing.
But if you think you're
so much better than me,
I can give you a competitor I
know you will find a challenge.
What do you mean?
[PICCOLO]
It's a surprise.
[grunting]
[gutteral gasps, groans]
[yells]
Ugh! What is that?!
Uh! No! Not another one!
[CREATURE laughs intensely]
Your name shall be Drum.
Your first official duty
will be to teach
this idiot a lesson.
[laughs]
What are you laughing at?
With looks like that,
I'm surprised you have
a sense of humor.
Piccolo! Arrrh!
You're finished!
[NARRATOR] Tien Shinhan was
prepared to fight King Piccolo.
But what of this new menace?
Will Goku arrive
in time to help?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!