[TAO yells]
[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
Goku fought Mercenary Tao for
control of the Four-Star Ball
in their second confrontation...
The young warrior's
first encounter with
the killer-for-hire nearly
destroyed him, as he endured
one bone-crunching
blow after another.
Fortunately, Goku was
prepared for the rematch,
thanks to the intense
training he received
from Roshi's old teacher,
Master Korin.
Desperate and near defeat,
Tao retreated to Korin's Tower
in hopes of acquiring
the legendary Sacred Water.
[TAO thinking]
All this artwork.
You'd think they could
carve some steps.
I can't take all this waiting.
There has to be
something we can do.
There is, and I've
put it off for too long.
Ha! I knew it!
You've got a plan, right?
Yes. To eat!
[UPA groans]
Hey! How come you're
not eating anything?
What're we gonna do?
I'll bet he's made it all
the way to the top already.
No problem. We'll take
care of him later.
Oh, I see. You have
some trick planned.
Otherwise you'd be
as worried as I am.
No tricks.
Aw, you can tell me, Goku!
What's your secret?
[GOKU yawns]
A good nap!
[UPA groans]
[GOKU snoring]
[UPA thinking] How can he sleep
at a time like this?
[GOKU giggling]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU laughs]
You're funny, Bulma...
All this time I thought
you were a boy!
Underwear!
[UPA thinking] Underwear?
What in the world
is he dreaming about?
[GOKU laughs]
Bulma! Don't be mad!
"Bul-ma"?
[ROSHI]
Mm-hm. Hm... Interesting.
[ROSHI laughs] I love reading.
So many great pictures!
I did it!
[ROSHI gasps]
[BULMA] I made a new and
improved Dragon Radar!
Oh, that's great.
Let me have a look.
See?
[ROSHI laughing]
You pig!
[ROSHI yells]
Ah! Hey!
[BULMA screams]
Huh?
[ROSHI laughing]
You're revolting!
Wait a second!
I only bought that book
for the compelling articles!
Yeah, right!
How can you waste
your time with that smut
when your best student
is lost and in peril!
[ROSHI laughs]
Of course you were
very productive
building that useless radar.
Spare me your sarcasm.
It will work. We have
a problem, though.
It seems someone is
jamming the frequency!
Hm...
Isn't there any way we
can scramble their radars
without losing ours, too?
How is this an improvement?
Now nobody can find
the Dragon Balls!
Including us!
I'm sure that
Tao will bring back
the ball once he finally
destroys the kid.
Well, he sure is taking
his sweet time about it!
[STAFF OFFICER]
He'll probably be back soon,
but it's a good thing he
doesn't charge by the hour.
[RED growls]
[TAO]
Ah! At last! The top!
The water is mine!
Who in their right mind
would live in such a place?
Hm. What do we have here?
Looks like tap water to me.
What is this thing?
[KORIN]
Yeah, does a number
on a guilty conscience,
doesn't it?
Huh?
Who might you be?
[KORIN]
I'm Korin, Keeper of the tower.
Korin? You?
[KORIN] That's right. You're not
from around here are ya?
You'd be wise to
show some respect.
That's quite an ego
for a little kitty.
Kitty? Is that supposed
to be your idea of a joke?
[TAO] I've had enough
of this conversation.
The sacred water is
powerless without me.
Hand it over.
Fine then. Kneel over there
and look at the wall. Now.
You can't order me around.
No one's allowed to see
me draw the water.
That's just the way it's done.
Get on with it then.
[KORIN] If I remember correctly,
I told you to kneel!
Whatever. But don't
try to give me
some fake stuff, or it's
filet meow for dinner!
[KORIN]
Here you go!
[TAO]
It's the real sacred water?
Yes. Made from the
very same batch
that made the boy stronger.
[TAO growls]
Not to your liking?
I need to test
my strength first.
[KORIN]
Not on me, buddy!
No, I'll spar with
that pillar over there.
Dodon ray!
Now that's a strong column!
Well, it is sacred stone.
It doesn't get much stronger
than sacred stone.
So if this water is
genuine and I drink it,
I will be able to break
the pole to bits
with no trouble at all, right?
I am sure you will be very happy
with the results
of your little test.
Huh?
One of the brats.
It seems hopeless.
By now he must be
ten times stronger,
Goku won't be able
to beat him anymore.
What'll I do if he does
the same thing to Goku
that he did to my poor Daddy?!
He happens to be standing
in just the right spot.
If the water doesn't work out,
and you'd better hope it does,
I'll just drop this pot
directly on his head.
That's a pretty weird
and disgusting idea, big guy.
Well, why don't we see if
we have to resort to that?
Now the proof!
[KORIN] Remember, it's-it's
a very thick column
It's the moment of truth!
[TAO yells]
You will pay dearly
for trying to fool me!
[KORIN]
Just settle down.
I'll calm down when you
produce the sacred water!
Listen, the so-called
sacred water
is only plain tap water, and
that's exactly the same thing
the boy drank when he was here.
I'm done playing around.
Stop lying or I swear
I'll drop this thing.
[KORIN]
No, no!
[KORIN] Whoa, look, it just took
a little while for your ray
to take its full effect
on the stone!
I'm going to pulverize that
miserable brat this time.
You can count on it!
[KORIN thinking]
Whoa, that was a close one!
He was really gonna
crush that kid.
Eh, but I think my little
stunt did just the trick.
He thinks he's invincible now!
[KORIN]
Wait!
You want a lift?
Hm?
[KORIN]
Here!
I offer free limo service.
[TAO]
I'm supposed to ride on this?
Climbing down
from here is almost
as tough as the trip up.
You don't wanna
waste all your energy
on the way down, do ya?
[TAO grunts]
It looks like the kid's
date with destruction
has arrived early.
[BULMA] I won't stop working
on this Dragon Radar
until it works perfectly
with no interference!
There's no need
to worry about Goku.
But I feel in my heart
that he's in grave danger.
Ah! Heart trouble you say?
I'll check it out for ya.
[BULMA screams,
ROSHI grunts]
[GOKU yawns]
I feel great! I slept
really well last night.
Did you?
No, I couldn't sleep
because I'm too worried.
He's probably had
the water already!
It's only tap water.
What?! It's just regular water?
That's right! There's nothing
special about it at all!
But... huh?
[TAO thinking] Why did that old
cat insist I take his cloud?
I got the impression he
didn't exactly care for me.
Oh, well. I guess
that's his loss.
I'll never see him again.
[KORIN thinking] That was quick
thinkin' there, Korin.
We didn't need him
gaining extra strength
from the climb down
the tower, did we?
Now!
[TAO yelps]
[TAO screams]
[TAO screaming]
[TAO groans]
[UPA]
It's him!
[TAO growls]
What happened?
Ah! I'll get you
for that, fur ball!
You're back. Sooner than
I thought, too.
[TAO] I'm in a hurry
to finish you off.
Really? You look kinda tired.
Don't ya wanna rest first?
Of course not, you fool!
Now get ready to be annihilated!
Oh, yeah?
Please be very careful, Goku.
I will. And don't worry,
we'll get him for what
he did to your father!
Thank you.
Do you have any last words?
No I don't.
And I think we've talked
enough for today!
[TAO yells]
Witness the power
of the sacred water!
[GOKU gasps]
[TAO grunts,
GOKU groans]
[TAO grunting]
[GOKU groaning,
TAO growling]
[TAO yells]
[TAO grunting,
GOKU groaning]
[UPA gasping]
Snap out of it, Goku!
Oh, why did you let him
hit you like that?
[TAO grunts,
GOKU groans]
[UPA gasps]
[TAO cackles]
[TAO yells]
This is the end!
[GOKU groans]
Oh, this is awful!
[GOKU grunts]
[TAO cackles]
[TAO yells]
[TAO grunts,
GOKU groans]
[UPA sobs]
[TAO cackles]
[UPA gasps]
[UPA whimpers]
Oh! Not good.
That boy is really
takin' a beating
from that bully!
Hm. That little glass of water
made a world of difference.
[laughs]
You're out of your league!
It's too bad that you never
learned to stay out of the way,
you should have left the
fighting to the professionals!
[UPA whimpering, sobbing]
[GOKU grunting]
[TAO gasps]
You really did get better.
You're almost as strong as me.
[UPA gasps]
You're alive!
I've got to be dreaming!
I've been studying you!
You're breathing gives
away your next move!
[GOKU yells]
I will crush you!
[TAO grunts,
GOKU yells]
[TAO groaning,
GOKU yelling]
[TAO groaning]
That's better!
Great job!
[TAO groaning]
Ouch!
[TAO thinking]
I didn't even see him coming!
How does he move so fast?
I could have sworn there were
two of them pounding me!
It was like a pair of tornadoes!
You should quit.
[TAO thinking]
I can't surrender to a child!
I could never look at myself
in the mirror again!
Imagine the shame!
What do I do now?
[TAO]
I give up! You win!
Huh?
I admit my defeat.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry... [whimpers]
I'll never hurt anyone again.
Uh...
[UPA]
Huh?
Please let me go! I'm sorry!
I guess we can let you leave...
Do you think that's
all right, Upa?
[UPA]
Uh...
[TAO cackles]
Hey!
Accept this apology!
[UPA screams]
Ah! It's a bomb!
Sayonara!
You fools!
[GOKU]
Uh-oh!
[GOKU grunts]
[TAO yelps]
[TAO screams]
[GOKU grunts]
He's gone!
--[UPA] Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
--[GOKU] Yeah!
[KORIN chuckles]
Commander!
What is it?
[STAFF OFFICER] The homing
device that was attached
to Mercenary Tao's
belt has stopped
transmitting all signals.
What does that mean?
[STAFF OFFICER]
Perhaps he damaged it
fighting with the boy?
[BULMA]
I finally finished it! Yay!
[rapid beeping]
Now we have a dragon radar
that's immune to interference!
That's wonderful!
How about a soak in
the hot tub to celebrate?
Mm... Okay!
[ROSHI laughs]
[ROSHI groans]
Well, I can dream!
[rapid beeping]
That's weird.
I wonder why these two
Dragon Balls are together.
That must mean that someone else
is trying to collect
all of them, too. Huh.
I know!
[beeping]
[GOKU]
This place on the radar must be
the headquarters of
the Red Ribbon Army!
Okay, I'll go there and
pick up the other Dragon Balls
and meet you back here!
That's dangerous!
There's probably a whole lot of
them and I bet they're strong.
You shouldn't go by yourself!
But to make a wish
you have to have
all of the Dragon Balls,
including those two.
Please be as careful as you can!
Don't worry.
I'll be back real soon.
Hey, Flying Nimbus!
Okay, you stay here and
keep an eye on this place.
As soon as I round up
all seven Dragon Balls,
I'll hurry back and then we can
bring your dad back to life!
Great! You're a
good friend, Goku!
So long!
[NARRATOR] Goku sets off
on a course for danger,
as his quest for the
Dragon Balls leads him
to the front door of
the Red Ribbon Army.
How can one boy challenge
an entire empire...
...and live to tell about it?
Find out as the
final battle begins,
next time on Dragon Ball!