[cheering]
[NARRATOR]
Last time, on Dragon Ball...
So long!
[NARRATOR] The 22nd
World Martial Arts Tournament
kicked into high gear
as our heroes' demonstrated
impressive skills and strength
during the Elimination Round.
Yamcha made quick work
of his opponent,
while Krillin got from
underfoot of his adversary
by staying one step ahead
of the gigantic warrior.
[NARRATOR]
Though the fight was intense,
Krillin prevailed,
getting the upper hand
and turning the behemoth
on his ear... literally.
Unfortunately, the toughest
fighters were still to come.
Goku had his hands full
as he entered a match against
the formidable King Chapa,
a former champion of
the tournament whose infamy
still strikes fear in
the hearts of all who know him.
Goku doesn't know
who he's dealing with.
So what's the big deal?
He's one of the
strongest men alive.
[YAMCHA] King Chapa is an
extremely dangerous adversary.
The last time
he entered the tournament,
I heard he won without being
touched by a single opponent.
Fighters ready, and begin!
Don't be afraid, little one.
I'll stop before I kill you.
Thank you.
[NARRATOR]
Goku's first preliminary bout
is shaping up to be
a preliminary battle!
Today, on Dragon Ball!
Mmm. Poor Goku.
I can't think of
a worse opponent for him
to face in his first match.
Yeah...
The fear inside you swells,
but I'll replace it with pain.
I can handle it, but thanks.
[ROSHI thinking] I hope you
spent your time abroad wisely,
my young pupil.
This is not a fight
you'd care to lose.
[chuckles]
[CROWD gasps,
CHAPA groans]
That's a first.
[MAN] I knew I should have
brought my camera!
[chuckles]
Hmmm...
I was mistaken...
I am not dealing with
an ordinary child.
[GOKU laughs]
[chuckles]
Hm?!
[laughs, yells]
[CHAPA chuckles]
He did great.
[GOKU yells,
CHAPA groans]
[cheering]
[CHAPA groans]
[panting]
[grunting]
[YAMCHA and KRILIN gasp]
Chapa looks like
he's out for blood.
He'll now use the
Eight-Handed Technique.
Eight-Handed!
This guy must
buy his skills wholesale!
As if he needed anything else
to make him more dangerous!
Focus...
Now you will learn
why I am feared.
Hm...
[YAMCHA and KRILLIN gasp]
[grunting]
That's amazing!
Goku's dodging him.
How can he even see his hands?
[CHAPA groans]
[chuckles]
You shouldn't leave
your feet unguarded.
You will pay for your insolence!
[yells]
Where is he!
[CHEETAH] Up in the air!
--[ALL gasp]
--Oh boy.
He just made a big mistake.
Why do you say that?
[laughs]
What are you doing
hiding up there?
You're only
delaying the inevitable.
Come down here
and take your punishment!
You're finished!
[GOKU yells,
CHAPA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
--[GOKU] Yaaa!
--[CHAPA groans]
[ALL gasp]
Number 28 wins
the match by a knockout.
[CROWD cheering,
GOKU chuckles]
I've... never seen
anything like that before.
He actually stopped
his movement by
controlling his
breathing. Amazing...
Whatever Goku learned
over the last three years,
it seems to be
working for him.
I won, Krillin! That was fun!
You did great!
But don't use all of
your tricks in the beginning.
Save some for later.
Definitely. I agree with you.
That's why I'm saving
some of my best techniques
for the tournament finals.
--[KRILLIN] Ooh...
--[YAMCHA chuckles nervously]
[GOKU] I can't wait
to go up against
the most talented fighters,
like you guys.
Yeah, right. Uh, me too.
That'll be interesting...
[ROSHI thinking]
How much is he holding back?
It's possible that he's
now stronger than me...!
Fighter 178, number 178.
Please come to the fourth ring.
[ROSHI thinking]
Whatever happens,
I cannot lose this match.
[KRILLIN] Mr. Chun, Mr. Chun!
Aren't you number 178?
[ROSHI] Hm?
Good luck, Jackie Chun!
[OFFICIAL B] Begin!
[BEAR MAN growls]
[BEAR MAN] Huh?
[ROSHI thinking] Goku is
demonstrating a level of skill
far beyond his years.
He's doing things
I've never seen before!
Why is Mr. Chun
just standing there?
Maybe it's a new technique.
[BEAR MAN growls]
Gramps! Are you awake?!
[ROSHI thinking]
Could it be possible the boy
is stronger than me?
Has the student
surpassed the master?
If so, what good am I?
[growls]
[ALL gasp]
Hm?
[BEAR MAN growling,
GOKU yelling]
[ROSHI growls,
BEAR MAN yells, grunts]
[KRILLIN and YAMCHA gasp]
Eh? Heh?
Ten! Time up!
The winner is fighter 178.
Hm...? Wow, I guess
I don't know my own strength.
That was awesome!
Way to go, Jackie!
My gosh! You wouldn't
think he was that tough.
But, man, he's incredible!
Yeah. I'm sure he'll
make it to the final match,
so what's the big deal?
One thing is certain;
the finals are
going to be challenging...
and dangerous.
[gong rings]
[NARRATOR] Yamcha had no idea
how true his words were.
Some of the most gifted fighters
in the tournament's history
took to the ring, as the
Elimination Round heated up
in a blinding fury
of sweat and muscle.
One after another, warriors
fell and heroes were born.
Amongst these titans, Goku,
Krillin, and Yamcha stood tall.
Fighters ready, and begin!
[TIGER yells]
[laughing]
[FIGHTER grunting]
I give up!
[chuckles]
He's a better fighter
than I first thought,
albeit a little weak.
No, he's conserving...
for later.
[yells]
[wails]
Out-of-bounds.
Winner is number two!
[CROWD cheering,
YAMCHA chuckles]
No matter his strategy...
he'll soon find out
he's no match for me.
You're in great shape!
Thanks, you too.
[announcement tune plays]
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention, contestants.
We will now break
for a ninety-minute recess.
Yippee!
Time for lunch! Let's go!
[KRILLIN] Hurry up, Yamcha!
We'd better get there
before Goku eats everything!
Get your genuine
unofficial t-shirts!
[PUAR gasps,
OOLONG laughs]
Stupid net!
How could you mess that up?
[yells]
[OOLONG] All right,
one more time!
Of course, sir.
Watching Oolong blow all
his zeni is entertaining,
but I'd rather be
watching the tournament.
It's tough not
being able to see.
Don't worry, they're fine.
[OOLONG] Not again!
Okay, last time. Really.
[distant gunfire]
[BULMA gasps]
[shatters]
Piece of cake.
You're not supposed to
use live rounds!
This is a game,
not a shooting range!
I could put
a few holes in you!
No thank you!
Then give me my prize. Move it!
Here ya go.
A stuffed toy! Try again.
[SHOPKEEPER screams]
[LAUNCH] Why don't you get
some real prizes?
[BULMA] At least
Launch is having fun.
[CONTESTANTS chattering]
[KRILLIN] Here.
Anyone ever told you
you have horrible table manners?
I agree.
Aah!
This year's Elimination Round
is tough. Don't ya think?
Perhaps if you're not
as good as we are.
I'm not worried.
Krillin! Only a fool
would presume such arrogance!
[ALL gasp]
There's no room in the ring
for overbearing pride.
Closing your mind
to the prospect of failure
will only ensure your defeat.
Too bad.
But you sound more like
Master Roshi than Jackie Chun.
Hm?!
Yeah, you do.
I'd swear you were him
if you didn't
have so much hair.
Me? Master Roshi! [laughs]
Oh, I'm flattered.
That's a good one.
N-No, I'm just an
old man trying to impart
some of my wisdom
to you upstarts.
Heh. Besides...
I'm not that handsome.
[dishes breaking]
[TIEN] You miserable slug!
That jerk!
[CLERK] Please! Don't hurt me!
You pass this
waste off as food?!
The stench alone is enough
to make me lose my stomach.
After a hard day's fight,
I expect a decent meal.
So go cook one.
What?
[GOKU] What's wrong?
[TIEN] Oh, it's you.
[YAMCHA]
If you can't play nice,
I'm afraid I'm going to
have to ask you to leave.
Really? [scoffs]
I've seen you fight.
You're pretty good
for an amateur.
You think you're ready for me?
Yes!
[growls]
Here I am. Come get me.
With pleasure.
[chuckles]
Uh!
Don't do it. This is not
the time or place to fight.
Got it?
[YAMCHA gasps]
[TIEN] You could
have been killed.
Thank the old man.
Chiaotzu, we're done.
Why was he so upset?
Because he's a big jerk!
Hrrrm.
[NAM] Jackie Chun, huh?
[ROSHI] Hm?
Nam, it's you!
Hey, Nam! Long time no see!
Ah, Goku!
[GOKU]
It's good to see you again.
I will always be indebted
to you for helping my people.
Are you gonna
fight in the competition?
Yes.
Is your village
short on water again?
No. Our water supply
is fine now,
thanks to Goku and Mas--
[coughing]
Uh, I mean Jac--Jackie Chun.
You should see how
my people have flourished
thanks in part
to your contribution.
[ROSHI]
It was my pleasure.
[BOTH gasp]
Mr. Chun, I didn't know
you helped out Nam's village.
Oh, it was nothing.
This time I am here for myself,
to test my skills
against the greatest fighter
I have ever known.
I am looking forward
to our rematch.
Mmm?
Hm.
Ooh... Aah!
[yells]
Ooh!
[GOKU laughs]
I will fullfill my destiny!
[BOTH yell]
[NAM groans]
[FIGHTERS grumbling]
Sounds fun.
Which block are you in?
I am in block number three.
Too bad...
I would have liked
the chance to fight
an accomplished warrior
like yourself.
But no matter what happens,
we'll always be friends, right?
Yes.
[NARRATOR] As the second half
of the Elimination Round
got under way, nearly all
of the 182 competitors
had been defeated.
[grunting]
[OFFICIAL A] The match
goes to number one!
[NARRATOR]
Only eight fighters make it
past the Elimination
Round to compete
in the World Martial Arts
Championship.
Despite the odds,
all of Master Roshi's pupils
made it to the finals.
Even the Master himself...
as Jackie Chun.
[OFFICIAL B] A knockout!
The win goes to number 178!
His technique is flawless!
Mm-hmmm!
Hey! Look alive, fellas!
We're halfway to the goal post!
And, by the looks of it,
you're leading the pack, Jackie.
That was great, Mr. Chun.
From here on,
it just gets harder.
[OFFICIAL C] Medic, come quick!
Nam!
[running footsteps]
--[KRILLIN gasping]
--[YAMCHA] Aah!
Wake up!
Number 99 wins by a knockout!
He advances
to the Championship.
[grunts] You monster!
Is he all right?!
He sustained severe
injuries and head trauma,
but he should live.
Poor Nam.
[TIEN] That's unfortunate.
I should have hit him harder.
[TIEN]
Oh well, no one's perfect.
An amateur like that
has no business in the ring.
He may live,
but he'll never fight
in another tournament again.
[growls] Neither will you.
[ROSHI] No, Goku.
You hurt my friend!
Let me go!
[GOKU] Come back here!
[grunting]
Come back!
[TIEN chuckles]
[growling]
That's great!
I'm impressed, guys!
I guess you did
learn a thing or two
from Master Roshi, after all.
[KRILLIN] Speaking of
Master Roshi... Where is he?
I haven't seen him
since it started.
Wherever he is,
I'm sure there's trouble.
It's kind of nice.
I need a break from
the old man every now and then.
[ROSHI]
I'll tell you what you need...
[BULMA and PUAR gasp]
[ROSHI] A napkin.
And for your information,
I've been hiding
amongst the crowd,
watching the Elimination Round.
I come here
to see my boys fight,
not stuff my face with sweets!
So did you like what you saw?
[ROSHI]
Mm-hm! From what I witnessed,
I'd say all three of you
have improved a great deal.
I think we have a strong shot
at winning this title.
Thanks.
We'll win, Master.
[announcement tune plays]
[ANNOUNCER] The Championship
is about to begin.
Will all competitors
please report
to the temple at this time.
[announcement tune plays]
[growls]
It's on, guys!
Maybe the rest of you
can find a good place
to catch the action.
[OOLONG] With Launch here,
anything is possible.
She's good at making room!
Follow me, boys.
My friend and I will show you
the best seats in the house!
[ROSHI and KRILLIN
laugh nervously]
All right, people, listen up!
I want this path
cleared out on the double.
Let's go! Move it!
[CROWD screaming, yelling]
[gunfire]
[NARRATOR] And so the fight
for the Championship has begun.
Not with a whimper, but a bang!
Join us next time
on Dragon Ball!