[NARRATOR]
Previously, on Dragon Ball...
Tien Shinhan unleashed his
newest technique,
Quadruplication!
Goku was stunned
by the crafty trick,
as the Four-Tien Army attacked.
Goku attempted to combat
the overwhelming odds.
However, as the
match progressed,
it became clear that Tien's
relentless assault had
taken its toll on both his
opponent, and the crowd.
Though he considered
Goku an ally,
the three-eyed warrior was
determined to defend and renew
his title as
Master of Martial Arts.
[TIEN]
Focus!
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU] It wasn't long
before Goku struck back,
disrupting Tien's force
with a blinding light.
[GOKU] You made the first one
worse by breaking into four!
Ah! No!
[NARRATOR]
The battle was fierce.
But, in the end, Goku
proved to be unstoppable.
With mighty force,
Goku piled on
yet another victory
to his list of accomplishments.
[BOTH gasp]
[ANNOUNCER] Goku wins the
first match of the semi-finals
and now goes on to
the championship round
where the 23rd Master of
Martial Arts will be determined.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[PICCOLO JR.] Just enjoy the
adulation of the crowd, Goku...
[chuckles]
...while it lasts...
[NARRATOR] Junior was eager
to begin his next fight,
this time against a
mild-mannered Hero. Get ready.
The 23rd World Martial Arts
Tournament is about to continue!
[sighs]
You were terrific! No,
I need to show more excitement.
Goku, you were horrific--
I-I mean--you were terrific!
[GOKU laughs]
[CHICHI laughs]
Hey, let go.
Good fight.
[TIEN]
Yeah. He's definitely grown.
Our first fight lasted
forever, and I barely won.
This time around,
I barely kept up with him.
Goku can adapt
to any fighting style.
His technique is flawless.
He is the strongest
opponent I've ever faced,
and I believe he
was holding back.
[KRILLIN, YAMCHA]
Huh?
It's true. There's no
other logical explanation.
He didn't use
the Kamehameha, not once.
I can't wait for the rematch.
Wow! Tien is either very
brave or very... nuts.
[KRILLIN sighs]
Whoever fights Goku
in the final round
sure has their work
cut out for 'em.
This next match
is an important one.
It will determine who will fight
Goku in the final bout
for the title.
The outcome is unpredictable,
but one thing is certain.
This battle will be a spectacle
you won't want to miss!
So find a good view and get
ready to welcome
the mysterious Junior and his
unpredictable opponent, Hero!
That's me... Time to go.
[GOKU] ChiChi, I need to
speak with Hero, alone.
Can you wait outside?
[CHICHI]
Huh...?
Hmm...
Is that you, Kami?
Goku.
That's a good disguise. I had
no idea who you really were.
That was the point. This
human masquerade worked well.
You came to defeat Junior,
didn't you?
Why are you so
interested in him?
Because he must be defeated
and you can't do it.
Huh?
[gasping]
He is way out of your league.
No way! Are you sure?
Listen to me, Goku.
Junior is a destroyer.
He will annihilate you and
the entire human race
if he gets the chance.
To defeat him, you
must understand his mind,
and as you know,
we were once joined as one.
As Popo told you, Junior and I
are bound by the same fate.
Even if you could destroy
Junior, you would not,
for fear of killing me.
Popo... He should not
have told you this.
He was trying to protect you.
I'm glad I know the truth.
Now that you know,
can you honestly say
that you will destroy him
when the time comes?
If you do not commit 100%,
you will fail and
your race will die.
I can stop Junior
without ending his life!
You cannot betray who you are.
Junior knows this and he
will use it against you.
Your honor will be
his greatest weapon.
There is more at stake
here than just two lives.
If you can't see that,
then you have already lost.
You're wrong!
[ANNOUNCER]
Is this microphone on?
There seems to be some
miscommunication,
but don't worry,
the match will start soon.
Uh, Mr. Hero,
we're waiting on you!
Don't hold your breath.
The twerp probably ran away.
What's up?
[KRILLIN] Looks like he's having
a conversation with Goku.
With Goku?
I wonder what those two
could be talking about?
Whatever it is, they don't
want me around to hear it.
That's strange.
I had no idea that
they knew one another.
Look, Goku,
you are very skilled,
and I don't pretend to know
all the training
you've been through.
I left the bulk of your
studies up to Mr. Popo.
But I do know this matter
with Junior must be settled.
And I'm the only one to do it.
Please, you've got to trust me.
I know I can defeat Junior.
If I'm right,
you won't have to die!
I appreciate your concern, Goku.
You have an honest heart
and I have no doubt
you mean well.
I'll tell you a secret.
Death is a very scary
proposition, even for Kami.
[HERO] Have no fear. I will do
what I must, and nothing more.
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] Ah, ladies and
gentlemen, Hero has arrived!
[ANNOUNCER] Get ready! This is
sure to be an amazing battle!
[PICCOLO JR.]
For a moment,
I thought you had developed
a brain and threw in the towel.
[HERO] Oh, ho-ho! Sorry.
This is a big arena.
I got lost on my way here.
[laughter]
Somebody should have
drawn him a map!
Next time, open your eyes!
[HERO laughs]
[CROWD laughing]
Hero seems like such a clown.
I just don't see how he could
be strong enough to beat Yamcha.
Perhaps being disarming
is part of his strategy.
[ROSHI chuckles]
Yeah. Just like me!
Heh! He's a buffoon by skill.
Yours is all natural.
[ROSHI groans]
Uh, hey! Be nice!
[BULMA] Look! There's something
different about Hero this time.
He looks serious.
[CROWD cheering]
[GOKU thinking]
Why didn't you trust me, Kami?
You don't have to do this.
[KRILLIN] Hey, Goku.
What were you two talking about?
Ha,ha. I'll tell you after
the fight. Everything's fine.
Right.
I hope.
Geeet ready! The second round
of the semi-finals begins now!
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
Why the serious look, old man?
Don't fear.
I won't hurt you for long.
You'll be dead before you
know it. I want Goku!
[chuckles]
Is that the extent of your plan?
Destroy Goku, rule the world?
Your vision is as lackluster
as your flawed heritage.
Piccolo!
[PICCOLO JR. gasps]
So pathetic, you were
always the weaker half.
Wh-What do you mean?
Who are you?!
I know all about you!
It looks like they're
having an argument.
Yes, I definitely
sense some tension.
[yells]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
Hold on!
[screaming]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU gasps]
Tell me! Who are you?!
[HERO gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[HERO screams]
[PICCOLO snarls]
[grunting]
[CROWD cheers]
[HERO growls]
[cheering continues]
[TIEN gasps]
What? How? I mean, they flew
with the... I mean, wow!
[HERO growls]
[gasping]
If you're having trouble seeing,
ladies and gentlemen,
don't be alarmed.
It's not your eyes.
These two seem to be moving
with superhuman speed!
Yeah, you can say that again.
Huh... This fight is peculiar.
Hero is attacking Junior
like they're at war.
For him, this seems personal.
[growls]
[PICCOLO JR. thinking]
Judging by his physique,
I should be able to defeat
this human with a look.
But his fighting style
is similar to mine.
How is this possible?
[HERO growls]
[yelling]
He's coming straight at me!
[shouts]
[yells]
[gasps]
--[HERO growls]
--[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[HERO gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
Time... for you
to say... goodbye.
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[HERO screams]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
Hero's strength is astounding!
Uh. How is it possible for any
human to do what he just did?!
Who is he? He's not a
human, that's for sure.
Maybe. It's outrageous.
Whoever he is, his powers
seem almost limitless.
[KAMI thinking]
He's been busy.
His fighting skills
have improved.
I had hoped my disguise
as a human being
would throw him off guard.
Unfortunately, any tactical
advantage this form brings
is wasted on that
pompous upstart.
Oh, really? Disguised
as a human being.
Reading minds is
dirty business, Piccolo.
[gasps]
You! Did you really think
you could fool me
with that fragile disguise?!
Your hand has been played
and you've been unmasked.
I can't understand a
single word coming out of
either one of their mouths.
It's like they're speaking in
an entirely different language.
You're... not alone.
I'm confused, too.
What do you think
you're doing here, Kami?!
Hmph. I'm sure my visit
comes as no surprise to you.
But then again, you
always were a little slow.
You know our fates
are intertwined.
You won't do
anything to hurt me.
I've come here to stop
you, one way or another.
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[ANNOUNCER] Both Junior and Hero
are speaking a similar language.
Unfortunately, it's unlike
anything we've ever heard.
But the meaning is clear
in any tongue.
These two warriors are out
to get one another! I think.
Whatever they're saying, they
don't want us to know about it.
Where's a translator
when you need one?
Hmph!
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[laughs]
You're bluffing! There's nothing
you can do to stop me
and you know it!
Did you really think
you could come here
and talk me out my quest?!
I was born to rule everything,
including this backwards planet!
Your skills have improved,
but you're as deluded as ever.
[HERO chuckles]
[HERO] You're right. Whatever
befalls you, happens to me.
And I'm just fine with that.
[gasps] You're insane!
You'd commit suicide?!
Whatever they're saying,
Junior doesn't seem very happy.
It's a matter...
of life and death.
Your concern is
touching but unnecessary.
The humans showed me a way
to get rid of you
without harming myself.
Huh?! What are you going to do?
[GOKU thinking] Kami's up to
something, I can tell. But what?
[HERO chuckles]
Uh, Hero has revealed a bottle,
and placed it on the ground.
It doesn't register as a weapon
so... the match will continue.
However, he may be attempting to
cast a spell on his adversary.
Look out!
You ready for your new home?
No, not that!!
[HERO]
Evil Containment Wave!
Oh, no!
--What?
--He's using a bottle?
[gasps]
[HERO yells]
[screaming]
[PICCOLO screams]
[HERO yells]
[screaming]
Just once I'd like to see a
normal fight!
He's using the same technique
that Master Mutaito
used to lock up King Piccolo!
Kami!
[screaming]
It's anyone's guess as
to what's going on here!
But one thing is clear,
the light unleashed by Hero
has begun to enshroud Junior!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
You've sealed your fate, Kami!
[gasps]
That looks fun. Can I play?!
Evil Containment Wave, reversed!
[PICCOLO JR. growls, yells]
--[screaming]
--Hero, look out!
[screams]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[laughs]
[screaming]
Everyone, uh, hang on!
[PUAR shrieks]
You tricked me! But if I am to
be imprisoned, then so be it.
But I will not condemn
this body to my fate.
Go now. I release you!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[KAMI screams]
Ha! There you are!
You may have defeated me,
but you won't win!
It's up to you, Goku!
Destroy him! Destroy him!
[GOKU screams]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[KAMI screams]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[gasping, whimpering]
[PICCOLO JR. thinking]
What will you do, boy?
The Evil Containment Wave
is the only thing
that could have stopped me,
and it failed!
Nothing will stand in my way.
This world is mine!
[GOKU whimpers]
[NARRATOR] Now that
Kami has been captured,
Goku must face Junior alone.
Can he defeat his deadly
opponent
or will he be conquered,
as Kami feared?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!