[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
the tournament semi-finals
erupted in a fist-storm
as Tien Shinhan
battled Jackie Chun.
Tien illuminated the match
with his Solar Flare,
blindsiding Jackie.
[NARRATOR] It looked
as though Tien's
surprise attack worked, until...
Thanks.
He's up! It's miraculous,
but the fight is still on!
Tien. There's a better way.
Let me help you
unlock your true potential.
Ka... me...
...ha... me...
He wouldn't!
Ha!
[NARRATOR] After the light show,
the real surprises began.
You're fighting a losing battle.
Anything you use on me,
I can send right back!
You could do with
a little humility.
I could teach you that, too.
[NARRATOR]
Despite Tien's protests,
Jackie attempted
to sway his allegiance.
That was somewhat encouraging.
Now let's just hope
that some of that sinks in.
[NARRATOR]
With that, Jackie Chun did
something
completely unexpected.
[yells]
[ALL gasp]
Aah! Whether by
accident or design,
Jackie Chun is out of the ring.
Tien Shinhan is the winner!
[NARRATOR]
And now, on to Match Six!
[CROWD whispering]
Jackie Chun's self-imposed
dismissal has stunned the world!
The question on everyone's mind
right now is: Why did he quit?
[CROWD chatter]
Jackie, how do you
respond to this?
[GIRL sobbing]
[CHUN]
Are you deaf?
Move your foot!
[MAN]
Er--sorry.
[CHUN]
There now, stop your crying.
[chuckles]
Where does he think he's going?
I think he's going away.
[CROWD cheering,
cameras flashing]
[REPORTER B] How does it
feel to beat the champion?
[REPORTER C]
Tien, say something!
--[TIEN] Get lost!
--[ALL gasp]
[chuckles]
Nicely done. Your performance
was exceptional, Tien!
[CHIAOTZU]
Mmm! Good work.
[chuckles]
Oh, I just love to win.
And seeing Roshi fail
was a bonus.
[laughs]
And now we move
to the final match!
[TIEN] Excuse me, Master,
but I'd like to get some rest.
--[SHEN] Eeeh?!
--[CHIAOTZU] Huh?
[TIEN] Why did he give up?
Why didn't he finish the fight?
I'd like to believe Master's
story about Roshi being scared.
But I know better.
There was no fear in
his eyes. He was in top form.
It doesn't make sense!
Silence!
[CHUN]
The truth is always upsetting
when you choose to live a lie.
You bow to a false master.
I can unlock
your true potential.
Leave your evil ways behind.
You shouldn't stress out.
It makes you lose your hair!
Stop! I won't listen to you!
[birds chirping]
[TIEN yelling]
Curse you!
You gave me a victory,
but you stole my resolve.
I want it back!
[ANNOUNCER clears throat]
The sixth and final match
to determine who will fight
in the championship round
is about to take place!
It's always thrilling
when teammates duke it out.
Today we'll see
Goku and Krillin,
both pupils of
the Turtle Hermit School,
fight to see which will
take on Tien Shinhan!
[CROWD cheering, hollering]
Goku and Krillin are fighting
each other? That's terrible!
Ah--eh, who do we root for?
We get to have
a match together.
Isn't that exciting?!
Uh. Uuh...
[KRILLIN]
Yeah, I'm ecstatic.
This gonna have more
suspense than a hayride!
[chuckles]
I'm tingling all over!
Uh! I just realized something.
Isn't this the first time
they've fought each other?
It's a first, all right.
And it could be the last
if they're not careful.
Who do you thinks gonna win?
I feel funny even guessing.
That's a tough call.
They're both very good.
It might just be a draw.
[LAUNCH]
The winner is obvious.
--[TURTLE] Uh?
--[ALL] Huh?
[LAUNCH]
Don't act surprised.
The answer's obvious to
anyone with even half a brain.
Of course Goku's
going to be the winner.
[ALL gasp]
Okay... And one step...
and two step...
and three step...
and four step!
Goku!
Promise me that
when we get in the ring,
you'll fight me like an
opponent and not as a friend!
I promise.
[drum tempo increases]
And now... Goku and
Krillin enter the ring!
[CROWD cheering]
Uh. Oh nuts! Who am I
supposed to root for?!
Goku! Oh, no...
Uh, wait. Krillin!
Hey! Are you trying to push
the odds in favor of Krillin?!
You sound like
a Goku sympathizer.
How could you turn
your back on Krillin?
I thought you were
supposed to be his friend!
Uh! But I didn't say that.
I can't take it anymore!
[KRILLIN] I've worked hard
the last three years
for a shot at
becoming the Champion.
[KRILLIN] I pushed
myself to the limit.
Every day I raised
my expectations,
and I exceeded them!
It was painful,
but I knew that
nothing worth having
comes without sacrifice.
And there's nothing I want more
than to win this tournament.
To show all the people
who put me down
how wrong they were.
I'm not a loser.
I'm Krillin! And I won't
be pushed around anymore!
[KRILLIN] This is it!
Now's my chance.
And I'm gonna take it!
It's time to fight.
Get ready... and good luck!
You too. Good luck!
[drum tempo increases]
[ANNOUNCER]
Ooh!
All right... On to Match Six!
[ALL gasp]
And begin!
[ROSHI] I've known all along
this day would come.
Still, I can't help but feel I'm
saying goodbye to an old friend.
--[distant rustling]
--[ROSHI] Eeh?
Oh, well. So long,
Jackie Chun. I'll miss you.
[KRILLIN]
What's he waiting for?
[grunts]
[CROWD gasps, murmurs]
[GOKU] I hope he blinks soon.
My eyes are getting sore.
Tell me!
[ROSHI]
Mm?
Tell me why you
disguised yourself.
Why you created this
elaborate charade
only to quit right before
you reached the very end.
Did you even have a purpose?
Or was Master Shen right?
Were you too scared?
If you've got
an explanation for this,
you'd better start talking.
I am tired of waiting!
Here it comes!
[gasps]
[quavered exhales]
[sneezes]
[TIEN]
Ugh!
Whew! It's starting
to rain, isn't it?!
[ROSHI]
Oh, that was a good one!
A-hem!
Aside from some advice...
I'm afraid this is
all that I can give you.
[TIEN]
Hey!
Yes? Was there something else?
This isn't a game!
I hope no one steps in that.
I know you're looking
for answers, Tien.
But don't place too much
importance on this tournament.
It is merely
a checkpoint by which to
evaluate your skill,
not substantiate it.
There is no greatest.
Awarding a young man a title
which declares him Master of
Martial Arts is very dangerous.
It does nothing more
than feed one's ego.
That is why
I decided my students
would compete in the
tournament, but never win.
And Jackie Chun
was my insurance.
[chuckles]
No more...
thanks to Master Shen.
To be honest, I found
your monologue stale
and a little boring.
The subject.
But your performance
was quite good.
I didn't know
you were so theatrical.
You should give Pamput a call.
Maybe do a buddy picture.
I'm sure he's got the time.
Roshi! It's a good
thing Chun retired...
while he still had a choice.
[ROSHI] You're right. It was
time for Chun to step down.
But it had nothing to do
with Shen's little stunt.
It was timing... since you're
going to take his place.
What?!
♪
[KRILLIN grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[TIEN] So you quit because you
thought I'd take your place.
I've been waiting
for you a long time.
Or someone like you.
The point is, there's a whole
new generation coming up
that needs guidance, and
frankly, I'm just too tired.
I need a replacement.
You fit the bill nicely.
The world could use
a few new heroes.
A new hero...
You're still rough around
the edges, to be sure.
But you hold promise.
[TIEN]
Uh?!
[ROSHI]
You're not ignorant.
And for your generation,
that's saying alot.
We definitely need
to work on your issues,
like that killing thing,
but you know that.
It's why you're
questioning your path.
It's what brought
you to me now.
[TIEN] Wrong! I wanna
be a killer. I like it!
A fish might
want to walk on land.
That doesn't mean
it's going to happen.
It's getting late and I'd
like to enjoy the sunset.
Did you have any more questions?
You fool!
Goodbye.
Everything you
talk about is a joke!
What could you teach me, huh?!
How to hide? How to walk away?
Who are you to
judge me or my master?
So I don't walk
the straight and narrow,
at least I'm not a quitter!
You talk about truth
and goodness as if
it's the path
to enlightenment.
Well all it really is is a
choice, and I've made mine!
You don't get it, do you? What
you choose to label as evil,
I call a good time.
I'm a killer, like Tao!
[ROSHI]
Ah, yes. Mercenary Tao.
He was a killer,
some say a natural.
However, your skills in that
department are mediocre at best.
You'll never measure up to him
because you have a conscience.
But don't take my word for it.
You know what's best.
Go get 'em, killer!
[TIEN grunts]
I-I will, you'll see!
I'll--I'll be better
than Tao ever was!
[grunting]
I'm getting dizzy.
Who's winning?
They're even.
[GOKU yells]
[KRILLIN]
Hm? Ah!
[CROWD gasping, chatter]
Attacking from behind--
that was smart.
I almost didn't sense you.
Thanks. The way you
dodged me was great!
Come on, guys.
They're both doing
fantastic! Don't stop!
We're behind you
all the way! Go, Goku!
Krillin, bust him up!
[BOTH]
Uh...
[grunts]
Don't look at me
like I'm crazy!
Why don't you people get
some guts and choose a side?!
--Come on, Krillin, go! Go!
--Yeah, Goku! You can do it!
Yeah, Goku!
Krillin!
[CROWD cheering, whistling]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[ALL]
Yaaay!
[ANNOUNCER]
Hmmm.
[groans]
This is it. You're going down!
[KRILLIN]
Uh! Uhhh!
Aah!
[CROWD chattering, cheering]
[ROSHI] Eh! Big hair
should be outlawed.
[GOKU]
That's bright!
I did it! Even Goku should be
knocked out by that fall,
for at least ten seconds!
[TIEN]
Uuh!
[GOKU grunts]
[TIEN]
Aah!
[CROWD gasps, whispers]
[KRILLIN]
Mmm! Mm!
[ANNOUNCER] Krillin is in
for a big surprise
if he thought that fall
would do Goku in!
This latest development
leaves Krillin a sitting duck,
or floating as the case may be!
Goku now has the
opportunity to bounce back
and turn the tables
on his opponent!
He's right, Krillin.
It's my turn now!
He's not kidding. I'd better
think of something quick!
[inhales deeply]
[ALL gasp]
[ROSHI]
Hm?
[GOKU]
Whoa!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[GOKU chuckles]
[CROWD gasps, chatters]
Wow, folks! That's what
I call a creative defense!
It looks as if
being full of himself
has actually
paid off for Krillin!
By filling himself with air
and dodging Goku's kick,
Krillin has
regained his ground!
[ROSHI chuckles]
Nice job!
You've improved a lot!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Were you surprised?
Mhmm! I don't think I've
ever had this much fun
in a fight before!
Let's keep going!
[ROSHI] I need a replacement
and you'll fit the bill nicely.
The world could use
a few new heroes...
[TIEN grunts]
Heh. I'll show you old man...
just how anti-hero I can be...
...when I destroy Goku.
[NARRATOR] So far, Goku and
Krillin seem evenly matched.
Their struggle for dominance
has been neck-and-neck.
But for how long?
Who will win the match?
More importantly, will they
still be friends when it's over?
Find out on the next
action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball!