[NARRATOR] In the smoky air,
an evil plot is brewing
one as wicked as the man
who speaks it into existence.
[screeches]
[RED] Shhhhhh.
[RED] Kill him.
[NARRATOR]
It is a beautiful day.
One that does not
go unnoticed by Goku
as he soars across the sky
aboard his Flying Nimbus.
New to the world,
our young hero is captivated
by the splendor of the ever-
changing landscape around him.
However, he is about to
learn an important lesson:
Always watch where you're going.
Whoa-AAAHH!
Uh-Uh-haa-haa-uh!
AHAHAHYEYEYEYEAHAHAH!!!!!!
Whoa-wee!
[NARRATOR] Though Goku's
quest to find his Grandfather's
Four-Star Dragon Ball is
sure to be fraught with peril,
he never forgets
to enjoy the moment
and absorb the wonders
he sees before him.
Whether it's chasing
a herd of wild buffalo
across the open plains,
or diving into a soft nest
of fruit trees for an
afternoon snack,
Goku savors each experience
and takes nothing for granted.
Growing up in a mountain forest,
with only his grandfather
to keep him company,
Goku was isolated
from the outside world
and all it has to offer.
Both good and evil.
To him, a breadbasket is
as marvelous as
the stars in the sky;
but he has yet to realize
that it is he who
is truly extraordinary.
[GOKU] Y-u-m, y-u-ooh?
That's strange...
I wonder if this
thing is broken?
Whoa! Got one! Hahaha!
[roars]
[PILAF] No! Oh, no. No! Please!
Noooo!
Ahhh! Huuuh? Oh.
Emperor Pilaf?
Sire, are you all right?
Help me... Help me!
Hey. You're safe, sire.
I'm right here.
Huh?!
Oh, nothing like a
good stretch on the floor
to get you really
worked up, ya know!
He-he-he-he-he-he-he...
It's okay, sire.
Crying is therapeutic.
I've never shed a tear
in my life, Shu! Go!
[SHU] But, sire!
I have good news!
We've picked up a
Dragon Ball on the radar.
The signal is very strong!
[SHU] It's about 150 miles away
in the Southwest.
Really?!
Uh-huh!
Are you crying again, sire?
Shu, my slipper.
Uh, here you go.
You boob!
I was obviously laughing!
You are my true inspiration.
With you by my side,
the whole world will be mine.
Aww, I didn't know you cared...
[PILAF] I was talking
to the DRAGON!!!
Impressive.
You dolt.
[PILAF] So, the
Dragon Balls have begun
to show up on our radar, eh?
Perfect. They're as
good as mine already.
Wake up world,
and hail your new ruler!!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Daah! Hold on!
[SHU] Gotcha!
[SHU] Why did you go
and open the window?!
You know you're not supposed
to do that when
we're up in the air!
Just-get-me-back-inside!
Shu...! Help...! Pull...! Pull!
I'm sorry I called
you a dolt! Please!!
Shu-u-u-! Wake-up, help me!
I don't wanna die-e-e-e!
Wa-a-a-a-a! Shu-u-u-u-u-u!!!
[SMELLY BOY] I wish I had
something to eat...
[SMELLY BOY] Yeah, well.
Lying here all day isn't
gonna make my belly full.
Guess, that means
it's time to go to work!
Ha-a-ahh!
Hahahaha! Yeah!
Boy! That was refreshing.
Huh? Wh-uh-
Where did all
my things go?!
Man, that kid was loaded!
I bet I'll make a fortune
on all of this great stuff!
Sure is breezy up here...
[sneezes]
I gotta find my clothes.
And my power pole!
That's it!
Power Pole... extend!
Huh?
Ohhh!
Power Pole extend!
Power Pole! Can you hear me?
[GOKU] Yeah! There it is!
Power Pole descend.
I guess whoever
took it ran away.
The dragon radar is missing.
That smell!
It's just like what I picked up
on at the pond
only much stronger.
Ohh.
E-e-e yuck!
Grandpa, if I don't
get the radar back,
there's no way I'll
find your Dragon Ball.
That smell might
lead me to the thief.
Guess I'll...
follow my nose.
[PILAF] Mai, are you sure there
is a Dragon Ball
somewhere around here?
[MAI] Yes, it's here.
But we have yet to
pinpoint its exact location.
Our radar confirms it's
within a one-mile radius
from the center of this town.
We'll find it, Sire...
It's just a matter of time.
Time is something
we don't have.
For all we know,
someone else could be
collecting one of the
Dragon Balls as we speak.
I won't risk a repeat
of last year's disaster!
I want all 7 balls secure and
in my possession, understand?
I want nothing less
than perfection
from every member
of this organization.
Remember, if even one
of the balls is missing,
the rest are useless.
As will be my need for you!
[SILVER] Good afternoon.
You'll have to excuse
the temper of my men.
We've been traveling all day and
it's left them a bit irritable.
Mmm. Something smells good.
But I can't stay for dinner.
Work's got me swamped.
You see I'm searching for
something called a Dragon Ball.
[SILVER] Perhaps you good people
could tell me where it is.
Before something
bad happens.
[FATHER] Please! Leave us alone!
We don't have
what you're looking for.
Really?
Pity.
It's a shame to raise
children in a broken home.
Destroy...
...everything!!
[crashing, cracking sounds]
[FATHER] Please, stop!
[SMELLY BOY] Hey, mister!
[SMELLY BOY] Hi!
Eh, you again.
Don't come any closer!
You smell.
S-o-o-o...
What do ya think'a this baby?
Pricey stuff, huh?
Hmm... Maybe, maybe not...
[SHOP KEEPER thinking] This
gizmo could be worth millions!
Whatever it is.
It must be something important.
How much will ya
pay me for it?
Uh-- This thing? Hmm...
Ten zeni, and that's just
because I like you, kid.
[SMELLY BOY] Ten zeni. Ten
zeni?! For what, the strap?
Hey, I'm trying
be nice here, kid!
You don't even
know what this thing is,
so how am I supposed to sell it?
You're lucky I'm paying
you that much for it!
Ten zeni. Take it, or leave it.
Some deal.
All right... Ten zeni.
Heh-heh! Smart boy!
Yep...! Enjoy!
Yeah, no more onion
sandwiches for this kid!
See ya! Wouldn't
wanna be ya!
Take a bath!
[PILAF] So, what do you think?
Too much?
Do you think it would
clash with my outfit?
No. I think it brings
out your color, sir.
[SHOP KEEPER]
Hello. I must say
you're making an
excellent choice today.
That crown is over
300 years old.
It was worn by
Alexander the Great.
He built a kingdom
to the North of us.
And now it looks to
have chosen a successor!
According to this label,
his nickname must
have been Ralph.
It is the symbol
of power worn
by many great historical
leaders, your majesty!
Why don't we step
into my parlor
where it's cool so we can
discuss this matter further?
That would be fine.
Pilaf, may I remind you we
don't have time to shop today.
That's Emperor Pilaf
and I can't rule the world
without a proper crown!
[PILAF] Eh, heh.
[SHOP KEEPER] Right this way.
Peeyuuw!
[GOKU] Hey! You!
Stop! Hey, you! Stop!
[GOKU] I know you
stole my Dragon Radar
and I want it back.
I sold your thing
to a shop keeper...
He gave me ten zeni.
I'll split it with
ya if ya want.
Where is he at...
and how do I get there?
[SHOP KEEPER] As you can see,
we have much more
than crowns to choose from.
Take your time...
We have the finest selection
of antiques anywhere.
Guaranteed.
It is an impressive collection.
But what I'm interested in can't
be found in any antique shop.
You search for
something unique, yes?
Something rare and
out of the ordinary?
Extraordinary!
With the power
to rule the world!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-!!
Why don't you put
it on a billboard?
Ah, I see...
There is one item I have that
possesses such potential...
A powerful relic.
Inherited by kings.
One after another,
for thousands of years.
[PILAF] So, if only kings
have claimed this treasure,
then it is my
obligation to own it!
He-he-he-he-ha-ha-ha!!
If you were not a king--
I wouldn't have
even mentioned it.
We can't let peasants
taint what belongs to royalty!
It is said whoever attains it
is master over all
creations under the sun
and wields enough power
to dominate the world.
Life itself would
bow to your will.
Domination.
Over the entire world.
No more monkeys!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
It can... control
monkey beasts?!
Absolute power.
And it's even gift-wrapped.
[PILAF] A Dragon Ball!
You were right, Mai.
Thanks, I usually am... sir.
Now, let's talk
price shall we?
I'm a reasonable man--
Is that enough?
[GOKU] This must be the place.
Found it!
Uh...
It shows the Dragon Ball
is right here!
Huu-uuh.
That fool--
He didn't even
know what he had!
We're off to a good start, Mai!
At this rate, I'll be ruling...
Ahhhhh!
You again! You're a--
Monster!
Don't come any closer!
This Dragon Ball is mine!
You hear me...!
I bought it fair
and square, monkey boy!
So step off!
Wait! How many
stars does it have?
Get your own.
How many stars
are on that BALL?!!
[SHOP KEEPER] Four.
Huh?
Four beautiful stars
on that ball, son.
That's Grandpa's Ball!!
Stop running!
Hey, you! Stop, now!
Huh?
[PILAF and MAI] Hey!!
What is that thing?
Come to me,
Flying Nimbus!
I'm coming!
Hang on Grandpa!
[MAI] Sir, something's
wrong with the Dragon Radar.
What?!!
[MAI] I'm over here.
What kind of problem?
The readings we're getting
from the radar system
don't make any sense.
Our position is here,
but the radar shows
the Dragon Ball signal is
occurring outside the ship.
Huh? Ohhh...
It just so happens
I have such an artifact.
Wait here. I'll be
back in a moment.
[SHOP KEEPER]
This should do the trick.
Just in case.
[SHOP KEEPER] Here you are.
I trust this is the piece
you're looking for? Eh?
[SHOP KEEPER thinking]
Come on, take the bait!
Not quite.
Not good.
It's fake!
It's just a glass bead!
[SILVER] You lied.
No, uh... No, wait!
That was the real deal, honest!
These whatchamacallits are
fragile antiques: priceless!
Dragon Ball.
Priceless and unbreakable.
But I--
[SILVER] Shhh.
It's here, somewhere.
Buried in all this crap.
Think very carefully.
The next word you
say could determine
the quality of the
rest of your life.
[SHOP KEEPER] I... uh...
Time's up old man.
[SILVER] Do it.
Nooo!
[gunshots]
A boring
conversation anyway.
Find it.
[NARRATOR] It looks like the
future of this Dragon Ball
is up in the air for now.
The race is on.
But who will win
the ultimate prize?
And will Goku be able to
defeat the combined threat
of Emperor Pilaf and
this sinister military unit?
There's only
one way to find out.
Stay tuned for the next
unbelievable episode
of Dragon Ball!