[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
Goku and Yajirobe were
paid a visit by Cymbal,
servant of King Piccolo,
and charged with
retrieving the Dragon Balls.
Yajirobe, unwilling
to part with his,
fought the monster in
a fierce battle and won...
[NARRATOR] ...cutting short
Cymbal's reign of terror.
[NARRATOR] Goku was astounded by
the mountain boy's strength.
Tambourine tracked down Yamcha
and attempted to make
him the eighth victim
among the Martial Artists
he was sent to slay.
He may have succeeded if it
were not for his master's call.
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Tambourine!
Wait.
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Cymbal was destroyed.
Our response to this crime
must be swift and severe.
Abandon your current assignment
and find the assailant.
[NARRATOR] Tambourine
was off to kill again.
[rumbling]
[ORANGE BEAR] Ahahahahaha!
Are you sure you
won't change your mind?
What do yee think?
I was the first to
find this. It's mine!
You don't need
that ball. Do you?
It's simply a shiny trinket,
pleasing to the eye.
But I can tell
from your reaction,
it holds a great value,
at least to yee.
[ROSHI]
What is it you want? Money?
[ORANGE BEAR]
Arr, how about a million zeni?
[ROSHI] A million?!
[TIEN] You can't be serious.
[ORANGE BEAR] You heard me,
old man! [chuckles]
Take it or leave it!
[ROSHI]
You drive a hard bargain.
[chuckles]
[ROSHI hums]
[ROSHI]
Tell ya what...
I'll give you this.
And what's that?
A lottery ticket
and a beer coupon.
Take it. Treat yourself.
[growls]
Forget it!
Okay.
[BOTH sigh]
[ORANGE BEAR]
Boys!
Negotiations are over.
Too bad I don't have a plank.
I didn't want this
to get out of hand,
but you leave me no choice.
I need that ball.
[TIEN growls]
[growls]
Chiaotzu!
Fire!
[chuckles]
Huh?!
[ROSHI] Ah, those
coupons are looking
pretty good about now, huh?
[TIEN]
Hmmm...
[TIEN chuckles]
Huh?
Ah!!
[ROSHI]
The Dragon Ball.
[ORANGE BEAR]
Awwww...
Thank you. Heh heh heh.
[YAJIROBE]
Why are you following me?
[GOKU] I told you.
If you keep the Dragon Ball,
you'll be attacked
by the monster.
[YAJIROBE]
Are you threatening me?
[GOKU]
No.
[YAJIROBE] So, then you
must be trying to scare me
thinking I'll give it to you.
Is that what you're up to?
[GOKU] No, I'm waiting for him
to attack so I can destroy him.
All you really want is the ball.
I do need your Dragon Ball.
Would you mind if I borrowed it
once I find all the others?
[YAJIROBE]
I said no!
[GOKU]
I'm telling you the truth.
I just want to get Krillin back.
[YAJIROBE]
Hmph. Do what you want,
but I'm not giving up
my Dragon Ball.
I'm selling it for a good price.
Hmm?
Stop chasing me!
I'm after the Dragon Ball,
not you, Yajirobe.
Yeah, right.
[YAJIROBE thinking]
Boy, this guy's super fast!
I'm not leaving you
until I find that monster.
[growls]
I want him! I'll tear him apart!
Uh, Master, calm down.
You need your strength.
[PICCOLO]
Uggh!
I'm worried for your safety.
What are you talking about?
Remember the nice cooker?
What do you think we got it for?
Emperor, I've got a bad feeling.
What if this doesn't work?
Be patient Mai.
It won't take long.
[TAMBOURINE telepathically]
Your Majesty?
[PICCOLO]
Hmm?
What happened?
Did you find the culprit?
[TAMBOURINE telepathically]
There's no one here.
Whoever I'm after,
they've moved on.
They moved? Pilaf.
Uhh...
Mai, the radar.
Yes, sire.
[beeping]
It... It's moving northeast,
at tremendous speed!
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Your target is headed northeast.
Hurry!
Yes!
[panting]
[beeping]
It's stopped moving!
Hmmm...
[PICCOLO telepathically]
The target is stationary.
New coordinates are NW0123.
Hmmm...
Hmm.
[laughs]
[grunts]
Hmmm...
[yawns]
[GOKU]
Hmm?
[YAJIROBE thinking]
Perfect!
[GOKU]
Aaah!
[chuckles]
That takes care of that problem.
Hmmm...
[PICCOLO]
What?! It's moving again?!
[beeping]
Ugh! This prey is slippery.
Tambourine, move fast. Get them!
[ROSHI]
Interesting. Hmmm...
It's this way.
The radar points there,
towards that old house.
I'll get it, Master.
[WOMAN]
Who's there?
Yes, what is it?
[TIEN]
Hi, I'm looking for...
Oh, there must be...
It's you!
You know him?
So, what is it you've come for?
Ahh...
[CHIAOTZU]
Huh?
Good, looks like
they know each other.
Yajirobe's way ahead of me!
I've got to catch up to him!
[chuckles]
Yeah!
Traveling in style!
Small world.
[MAN] Yes it is,
as bad luck would have it.
I thought I could
forget your face,
but I'm reminded of
it every time I move.
[crowd cheering]
He's had it! You've won!
Get back!
[MAN screams]
I had to be rushed
to the hospital.
I don't remember much, except
the pain from 13 broken bones.
It took me two years to
get back to this house...
...and my beautiful wife.
[baby babbling]
[RADIO] Seven members
of the Martial Arts Society
have fallen victim
to this unknown killer.
The culprit is still at large
with police getting
more anxious every day.
Come quickly.
[TIEN] I'm sorry
about your injuries.
I was a different
person back then.
So was I. I could walk
without using a cane.
The reason I've come is
I need your Dragon Ball.
[MAN] Dragon Ball?
What the hell is that?
A ball with a star mark.
We know that you have
it here, somewhere.
Will you give it to us?
No, now go.
[TIEN]
Unacceptable!
[MAN]
I don't know of what you speak.
Hmph.
[MAN] What's more,
I think you're lying.
[gasps]
Even if it did exist, help
is the last thing I'd give you.
Huh?!
Hmmm...
Oh, what a beautiful day.
Don't worry about Tien.
You just leave that up to me.
[motors]
Uh... Not good.
[TIEN]
I must have it.
You sound like a broken record.
Get back!
[TIEN]
I'm not here to hurt you.
[door opens]
Tien Shinhan, you're
under arrest for murder.
[TIEN]
What?!
Unlike the police,
it didn't take us long
to identify the killer,
Tien Shinhan.
Who else is as strong
and delights in maiming
Martial Artists?
No! That's a lie!
You would kill anyone
if it suited your needs.
I'm living proof.
You've got it wrong.
I'm not the one doing this!
The killer is King Piccolo!
[SERGEANT] Silence!
You can tell your story down
at the station. Take him!
Back off!
Why...
[ROSHI]
Stop it!
Huh...
[SERGEANT]
Hmm?
Huh?
Freeze dirt bag!
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
Huh?!
Uh, you must be...
Don't worry, sergeant.
I got him!
You idiot! Don't you
know who this is?
It's Master Roshi,
King of Martial Arts!
Uh?! Did you say king?!
Ah?!
[gasps]
Uh, Master Roshi, what are you
doing here with this criminal?
Sergeant, Tien Shinhan
is no murderer.
He's a friend of mine.
And we're on important business.
Yeah, but...
Let it go, Sarge.
I can assure you
that Tien is not guilty.
[SERGEANT]
Stand down!
The Dragon Ball?
Why do you bother asking?
Just tear the place apart.
That is your style,
isn't it Tien?!
Just hurry up
and get it over with.
I beg you, we
desperately need that ball.
Ah!
[TIEN] I apologize for
the wrong I've done you.
If you want revenge,
break an arm or two.
Whatever you want.
But please,
give us the Dragon Ball.
Huh...
I've dreamed of revenge
longer than I can remember.
[MAN sighs]
I forgive you. Get up.
[MAN] You may have
the Dragon Ball,
as soon as he wakes up.
[MAN chuckles]
[snoring]
Huh?
Old man, did you
kill my brother?
Huh?
Hmmm...
Hello.
What's the big idea? Hmm?
Ah ah! You're all crazy!
Well, what'd ya know!
What Goku was
telling me was true.
If you keep the Dragon Ball,
you'll be attacked
by the monster.
Uh. Hmmm...
[GOKU]
Hey!
Aw, that brat!
Huh?! No way.
You stay out of this Yajirobe!
It's my job to take
revenge for Krillin!
Aren't you dead?
I took care of you in the woods.
I told you I'd make you pay!
I'll never forgive you
for killing Krillin
or destroying my Nimbus Cloud!
And I want my Dragon Ball back!
Listen Goku, you can off
this monster if you want.
That's fine with me.
But you'd better
let me eat him! Agreed?!
[TAMBOURINE] Now I understand.
How embarrassing.
My young brother, Cymbal,
killed by a couple
of little rats!
[YAJIROBE]
Rat?! You take that back!
[TAMBOURINE chuckles]
This is truly hilarious!
You want to fight me again?
Last time you
didn't even touch me!
Last time I was hungry.
But now I'm full
and ready to beat you!
[TAMBOURINE]
Beat me?!
You're not even
in the same league!
[GOKU] I'll stop you,
one way or another!
You'll see!
This one's for, Krillin!
[NARRATOR] Will Goku
make good on his promise
and defeat Tambourine?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!