[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
the Sixth Match of the
tournament series began
as fellow Turtle Hermit
students Goku and Krillin
engaged in a friendly,
but volatile slugfest.
[NARRATOR] Punch-for-punch,
the amicable adversaries
stood their ground,
and occasionally left it.
I'll show how anti-hero I
can be when I destroy Goku.
[NARRATOR]
The battle went on and on,
with both opponents
taking their knocks...
and getting their kicks!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[ALL gasp]
[whimpering]
Puar, could you
whimper someplace else?
I can't help it.
Fighting scares me.
The fight's nothin'!
I'll tell ya what's scary.
What?
Your ugly face.
--[BULMA grunts]
--[OOLONG] Ow! Ooh!
Stop joking around.
This is serious.
[OOLONG] The sad thing is,
these are my friends.
Hm! You got me that time!
Neat trick! I've never seen
anybody do that before.
Hm! I didn't have much choice.
You rebounded pretty quickly.
You looked funny,
what's the name of that move,
the balloon technique?
Maybe. I'm not sure.
I've never named
a technique before.
[CROWD cheering]
Why is everybody cheering?
All they're doing
is talking to each other!
I've seen more action
on a playground.
[DOG BOY]
How does he do that?
[ROSHI] I must say,
both those boys
are in excellent form today.
Still, I can't
help but wonder
if Goku isn't
holding back a bit.
[GOKU]
Ka... me...
...ha... me...
Ha!
[yells]
[KRILLIN groans]
[PUAR yells]
[CROWD gasping]
Ooh. That hurt.
[CROWD murmurs]
[TIEN] I hate to admit it,
but that was good!
[ANNOUNCER]
Ah... It looks... painful.
Uh--I mean, it looks
like Krillin is down!
Aren't you going to
start the countdown?
Uh... One...
two...
three...
four...
five...
six...
[CROWD cheering]
Way to go, Krillin!
[ANNOUNCER] In what can only
be described as astounding,
Krillin has bounced back from
Goku's jaw-breaking assault!
That was close!
Come on, you didn't think
I'd let you win that easy!
[laughs]
--[GROUP laughs]
--[SHEN] Ridiculous!
What is this, the happy fight?
It's like watching
a bad reunion!
If your pupils weren't
maladjusted freaks,
maybe they'd be happy too!
I'm happy, see.
Of course. Pay them no mind.
Those underlings are jealous.
Jealous?! Our boys are
going to take yours down,
and you know it!
Yeah, sure,
whatever you say, schizo.
[yawns]
Calm down, Bulma. He's a jerk.
[yells]
Oh, kids today...
They're so predictable.
Take off your glasses.
Maybe you can see better.
You be quiet!
All right, Goku! Get ready...
Counter Attack!
[KRILLIN yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[KRILLIN groans]
[KRILLIN mutters]
[panting]
[KRILLIN] Get control of
yourself! You can do this.
All you need
is a good strategy.
Why am I talking to myself
in the second person?
And... for most
improved fighter,
the award goes to Krillin!
Or at least it should.
The kid's progress is amazing!
[KRILLIN] There's only
one way to win this!
Goku! You'd better
prepare yourself!
Ka... me... ha... me...
Krillin, don't. That wave
doesn't work on me.
If you use it, you'll
just waste more energy.
[KRILLIN]
Ha!
I told you it wouldn't work.
[GOKU]
Aaah!
Aaah...!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
I did it!
[laughs]
[laughing]
Sorry, Goku.
But let's face it,
your tail is
your only weakness.
[TIEN]
Uh! His weakness!
Looks like I win!
[laughs]
I hope you're
not mad at me, Goku.
I did what I had to do.
Just like you.
[ROSHI] Smart, Krillin.
Not very nice, but smart.
Neat trick, huh? I knew
the Kamehame-ha Wave
would distract you so I
could sneak up from behind!
Goku!
[ALL gasp]
[KRILLIN laughing]
[ANNOUNCER] For reasons
that are unclear,
Goku has collapsed on the stage
and appears to be unconscious.
This could be
the end of the match!
[KRILLIN laughing]
[ANNOUNCER clears throat]
One...
two...
three...
four...
Interesting... How did he
ever make it this far
with such a
debilitating weakness?
I suppose I should be
angry at Krillin
for taking Goku's defeat
away from me.
But whatever works.
[chuckles]
Krillin! Let go of
Goku's tail! Right now!
Why don't I have a tail?
Because you're a buffoon,
not a monkey.
[ANNOUNCER]
five... six... seven...
And eight... and nine...
[laughs]
This is it!
[FAN]
Hey Announcer, nice hair!
[ANNOUNCER]
Thank you. It does have
a nice sheen, doesn't it?
Oh! What am I doing?! Eh?
[laughs]
What the--?
--[GOKU chuckles]
--[KRILLIN groans]
Surprised?
I've been working it out.
Uh?
[KRILLIN grunting]
That's impossible! You can't
handle your tail being grabbed!
I know for a fact
you lose your energy!
[GOKU laughs]
Not anymore.
I got tired of
people grabbing my tail,
so I spent the last
three years training it.
Oohp!
[GOKU yelps]
Let's go.
[MAN chuckles]
I'm gonna... fall down.
[MAN] What should
I do with you?
My tail always seemed
to get in the way.
But Master Roshi told me the
only way I'd make things better
was to work it out,
so I did!
It's typical.
Go ahead and squeeze
it again. It's okay.
[ROSHI]
I think I did mention
something about
that in passing.
What do ya know,
they do listen!
[ROSHI] To have come so far
in three years is amazing.
He must have been on one heck
of a calisthenics program!
I shouldn't be surprised.
If Goku's tail is
his greatest weakness,
his determination is by far
his greatest strength.
Why, I imagine
that little boy could do
just about anything
he put his mind to.
[GOKU chuckles]
[ROSHI] He certainly
proves my point.
Success is more try than cry.
[GOKU laughs]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Too bad for Krillin.
How do you fight a warrior
without a weakness?
[GOKU laughs]
Hey! That wasn't fair!
Fair is not on today's menu.
That wasn't nice!
In case you hadn't noticed,
I'm not here to be nice!
Oh no, here we go.
This isn't going to be pretty.
[CROWD cheering]
[yells]
They don't look
like they're having fun.
It's getting... vicious!
Tear it up, Krillin! Do it!
Boys,
remember your friendship!
[KRILLIN yelling]
[CROWD cheering]
--[ALL gasp]
--[LAUNCH laughs]
[laughs]
Another strong attack by
the ever-surprising Krillin!
Goku rebounds!
Aah!
But... You just--
Auh!
[CROWD gasps]
Heh?
I hope everyone else saw that.
[KRILLIN]
Goku! Where are you?!
[KRILLIN] I know you're
still here! Show yourself!
Goku!
[ANNOUNCER] In what is
arguably the most
amazing feat ever
performed on this stage,
Goku has disappeared
right before our very eyes!
This isn't funny!
He's... vanished!
[distant boinging]
Cut it out! Goku!
Since when could he disappear?
It's astounding!
I've witnessed people
disappearing before,
but never for
this length of time.
[boinging tempo increases]
[TIEN]
Wait!
[TIEN] It's his speed!
He's moving so fast,
it gives the illusion
that he's disappeared!
What a fantastic way to
disorient your opponent.
Is there no end
to this boy's skill?!
[TIEN]
It's a flawless approach!
[rapid boinging]
[GOKU]
Ah-la-la-la-la!
[whimpers, yells]
Whoa! Goku has reappeared!
[TIEN]
That's it.
[CROWD cheering]
Krillin... is out.
Goku is the winner. Yeah.
All right!
[laughs]
Krillin, who seemingly
dominated Goku
throughout most of
the fight, now appears
completely flabbergasted
after his fall from the ring!
A surprising end
to a sensational match!
It's over?!
The fight was anticlimactic
and completely void
of any cathartic experience.
I didn't understand
a word you said.
[TIEN] The poor reaction
from the audience
is further evidence
of Goku's brilliant attack.
For while they focused
on his scare tactic,
they missed the eight punch
assault that followed.
Not to mention the
power-kick that sent Krillin
flying out of the ring.
[SHEN]
Now the fun begins.
I hope you enjoy
this small victory, Goku;
it will be your last.
[ROSHI]
Throughout the tournament,
Goku has demonstrated
remarkable progress.
Let's just hope
it's enough to get him
through his
next battle... alive.
[ANNOUNCER]
That concludes today's event.
Join us here tomorrow
for the final match
to see who will become the
next Master of Martial Arts!
I'm really sorry that you
lost the match, Krillin.
[KRILLIN] Mm. That's okay.
You were the better fighter.
Besides, I told myself I'd do
my best and that's what I did.
But I do have one question...
What?
[KRILLIN] How did you do
that disappearing thing?
[GOKU] No problem.
I'll tell you all about it.
Listen, I just wanna let
you know... that I think
both of you did
an exceptional job.
I don't know about
exceptional, but thanks.
You're exceptional. Don't
argue, I'm bigger than you.
Hey, you've got
a great left hook!
Take it from someone who knows.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Well, I want you to know I
rooted for both of ya... mostly.
It was great
having everyone there.
[KRILLIN]
Whadda ya say we go eat?
[GOKU]
Great! I'm starving!
[BULMA]
Are you ever full?
[LAUNCH]
Where are we goin'?
[OOLONG] It's a celebration!
The best place in town!
[LAUNCH]
Souds great. You're buyin'.
Enjoy your last celebration.
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Will Tien Shinhan
make good on his promise
to destroy Goku
in the final match?
Who will become the new
Master of Martial Arts?
The risks for our hero
have never been higher.
If Goku doesn't
walk away with the title,
he may not walk at all.
The thrilling conclusion of
the 22nd World Martial Arts
Tournament begins tomorrow.
Don't miss it!