[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku climbed Korin Tower in
pursuit of the Sacred Water,
a potion believed to
give increased strength
to whoever consumes it.
What he found instead
was Korin himself.
The wise guardian
agreed to give Goku
the enchanted liquid,
provided he could get it.
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR]
The young warrior fought hard
to wrestle the bottle
from Korin's paws.
But no matter what he tried,
the plump pussycat
stayed one step ahead of him.
[GOKU panting]
You can't be that tired. Come
on, we're just gettin' started!
[NARRATOR] As Goku continued
his relentless pursuit
for the bottle,
Korin revealed a shocking truth.
In 300 years, only one
person had ever managed
to capture the
Sacred Water from him.
Master Roshi.
[GOKU] Was he really fast?
How long did it take him
to get the bottle from you?
Whoa! Just three minutes?!
Three years.
[NARRATOR] Goku's quest for the
Sacred Water continues today.
Thr-Three years?!
It really took that long
for Master Roshi
to get to the Sacred Water?
That's right.
Now, how long do you
think it's gonna take you?
[KORIN laughs]
Stop that! It's not funny.
I have to get that
extra strength right now.
I don't have much time.
My friends are in trouble!
[GOKU growls] I'm going to
get that water from you,
whatever it takes!
[KORIN yawns]
The rain always makes me sleepy.
Huh?
The bottle will be right here
whenever you want it,
so just let me know.
And, try not to worry so much.
Three years can
go by pretty quickly.
Uh. But-But...
All right! That's it.
I'm getting that water!
I'm getting it right now!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU laughing]
[KORIN]
Ah, the ol' afterimage trick.
[GOKU laughing]
[KORIN chuckles]
Looks like I found
the right one here.
[GOKU]
Ha!
I've got you now!
[GOKU groans]
[KORIN laughs]
[KORIN] Thanks for the
entertainment, kid.
That was fun. Good night.
Come back!
I can still fight.
Once the room stops spinning.
[KORIN yawns]
[GOKU thinking] I can do this.
Just one more try.
[GOKU yells]
[stomach growling]
I forgot... I...
...haven't eaten
anything since yesterday.
Ah! That reminds me,
I haven't eaten anything
in five years.
Why don't we grab some lunch?
I know just the thing.
[GOKU snores]
[KORIN hums]
[KORIN]
Lunch is ready! Come get it!
Lunch?
[GOKU panting]
[KORIN]
Hungry?
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU panting]
Here ya go. Enjoy.
This is a bean! All I get
for lunch is a single bean?!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] Are you kidding?
This isn't fair!
One is all you need.
[KORIN]
It's a Senzu Bean.
Magical-- Just one will keep you
full for at least ten days.
But, uh, you have
to eat it first.
I don't think this is
going to fill me up.
I can eat a lot.
[GOKU burps]
Ah...
[KORIN]
You feel light-headed and weak.
But your appetite
isn't the problem.
At this altitude,
the air is much thinner
than you're used to,
so all that wasted energy
you're throwin' around
is bringing you back down. So,
you should move like you speak,
with purpose and
clear direction.
Commit your mind and focus.
Distraction is the
root of all failure.
What's this? Garbage?
[GOKU]
Uh-huh.
Then why keep it around?
[GOKU screams]
My grandpa's Dragon Ball!
Wait! Stop!
[GOKU]
No! What are you doing?!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU] I have to find it,
before those Red Ribbon guys do!
[KORIN chuckles]
[UPA sighs]
Where is it?
[GOKU grunts]
I found it!
[GOKU growling]
[UPA]
Huh?
I thought I saw
something moving.
But it couldn't have been Goku.
It was much too fast.
I think my eyes
are playing tricks on me.
[KORIN thinking]
Three hours round trip, not bad.
No better fuel than motivation.
[GOKU panting]
This isn't garbage, okay?!
It's the Four-Star Ball and
it's very, very important to me!
Hey! Are you listening to me?
It's not nice to throw away
another person's things! Korin!
[GOKU]
Wake u--
[GOKU screams]
[KORIN chuckles, laughs]
Hm. No, not like this.
I'll get it tomorrow.
The right way.
[GOKU snores]
[KORIN chuckles]
[KORIN thinking]
Well, well, well.
It seems honesty
isn't extinct after all.
I haven't been surprised
in over 600 years.
This boy is very special.
Not at all like his
old Master Roshi.
[KORIN laughs]
[KORIN humming]
[GOKU thinking]
Now's my chance.
[KORIN sighs]
[KORIN]
Tired...
[GOKU gasps]
[KORIN snores]
[KORIN] Concentrate.
Anticipate my movements.
Know my thoughts
by reading my breath.
Uh. Your breath?
How is that going to help me
get the bottle from you?
Well, it wouldn't hurt.
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU yells]
Huh?
[KORIN laughs,
GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] Though Goku
tried with all his might,
both the Sacred Water and
Korin's advice eluded him.
And so, the second day passed.
I know I hit him.
So how is it that he
managed to survive?
[TAO]
Oh. Of course. The Dragon Ball.
Hm...
[TAO]
No matter.
I only hope he's enjoying
today while he can.
For tomorrow...
Ha! He will see
his last sunrise.
[UPA] Goodnight, father. I hope
these flowers keep you warm.
Please hold on.
Goku says he can bring you
back and I believe him.
I miss you so much.
[GOKU yells]
[KORIN laughs]
[KORIN]
Hya!
[GOKU pants]
No more.
Then we will
retire until tomorrow.
Will I win?
Only you know the
answer to that question.
[KORIN thinking]
His progress is amazing.
I haven't been
this tired since...
...ever!
Goku, help me!
He's coming! He's coming!
[UPA panting]
[GOKU yelps]
It was a dream.
I'm trying, Upa.
But if it took
Master Roshi three years,
how long will it
take me? Breath...
How am I supposed to read
someone else's breath?
I'm so thirsty.
Hope there's none of those
weird snake things
in this one.
[BULMA] No, that is incorrect.
Now watch closely.
Bulma!
[BULMA]
Like this. Now you try it.
No! Do it right!
[GOKU laughs]
One, and, two, and...
[ROSHI grunting]
Stop it!
[GOKU laughs]
One and two...
[ROSHI grunting]
[ALL grunting]
[KORIN] Know my thoughts
by reading my breath.
Ah! That's it!
Okay... do what he does.
[KORIN snoring]
[GOKU snoring]
[KORIN grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[KORIN yawns]
[GOKU yawns]
[BOTH yawn]
Today is the day, Korin.
I'm going to get that bottle.
[KORIN]
Do, don't speak.
[GOKU yells]
[BOTH grunting]
Focus, boy!
[KORIN laughs]
[BOTH gasp]
No! The bottle!
[GOKU yells]
Don't! You're gonna fall!
Goku!
[GOKU giggling]
Look, I got it!
Hurray! I have the water!
[KORIN thinking]
Three days... he's ready.
Can I drink it now?
Drink up. You earned it.
[GOKU sighs]
Korin? I don't get it.
I don't feel any different
than I did before.
That's natural.
You feel exactly as you should
after drinking tap water.
What?! Tap water!
But it's supposed to be special!
[KORIN laughs]
Yeah, well not really.
See, you gained strength by
workin' hard to get that bottle.
Climbing up and down the tower
increased your endurance.
Learning to anticipate my
actions sharpened your mind.
And taking that bottle away
from me increased your speed.
So see, you've tripled
your strength since
you arrived all by yourself.
I'm ready!
[GOKU laughs]
[TAO]
Hm.
Good job, tailor.
But I should
cut back on my eggs.
[TAILOR]
Thank you, sir.
I had to stay up all night
to complete it.
Whatever.
Now I can finish this job and
retrieve the last Dragon Ball.
[TAILOR]
But, sir-- My money.
What? Tailor...
You desire compensation
for the privilege
of servicing the needs of Tao,
the great mercenary?
A simple token of appreciation.
Silence. I see...
I have given you my business
and in exchange you offer me...
...contempt.
[TAILOR gasps]
That's a bit too pricey...
You see, people meet my
needs freely, out of fear,
and if I were to pay you,
it would make me look weak.
I can't tolerate
that sort of reputation.
Please! Sir, I meant
no disrespect.
I only ask for what
is rightfully mine.
Yes. You have made that clear.
No-no-no-no-no--!
[TAILOR groans]
[TAO]
I believe I made my... point.
[GOKU grunting]
Very good, Goku.
You've learned all
that I have to teach you.
[GOKU laughs] Thank you,
Master Korin, for everything.
Farewell, young man.
[GOKU giggles]
Bye, bye. See you later!
[KORIN thinking] That boy is
gonna do great things.
He may even be more powerful
than his old master...
We'll just have to see.
It's time.
[NARRATOR] Goku and Mercenary
Tao race toward destiny,
as their final
confrontation draws near.
Next time on Dragon Ball.