[yells]
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
the tournament's final
match was in full swing
as Goku and Tien Shinhan
attacked one another
in furious combat.
[NARRATOR]
Using the Afterimage Technique,
Goku managed to confuse Tien
long enough to mount
a strong offensive,
which appeared
successful until...
[NARRATOR]
The young hero was stricken
by a mysterious,
paralyzing force
that left him vulnerable
to Tien's assault.
[GOKU]
Not fair!
So what?
[cackles]
[CROWD cheering]
That hurt.
[ANNOUNCER]
Four...
Five... This could be it!
[ANNOUNCER]
Six...
This whole thing
--is too stressful.
---[ANNOUNCER] Seven...
Goku stand up!
[ANNOUNCER]
Eight...
[YAMCHA thinking]
This isn't right.
You rely... too much on tricks!
Quit whining. Now, choose.
Either fight me or
step out of the ring.
Master, what just
happened to Goku?
[ROSHI thinking]
Something unnatural.
When you meet Tao, be sure
to tell him I sent you!
No way, I don't
give up so easily!
[SHEN] I don't think Goku
understands our position.
Explain it to him.
Do it again?
[GOKU grunts]
Incredible! Tien delivers a
power kick to Goku's face.
So forceful, it's like
an exploding bomb!
That kick was one chance
in a million!
Goku!
Uh-oh! Looks like Goku is headed
for a crash-landing
outside of the ring! Whoa!
A little to the right, Goku!
[cackles]
Oh, no!
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!
An outrageous recovery by Goku!
[BULMA, YAMCHA sigh]
Again.
[grunts]
[GOKU groans]
[growls]
[ROSHI thinking] Crane, your
foul stench is all over this.
Have you no shame!?
[YAMCHA thinking]
That was no accident.
It's as if Goku
were being... controlled.
Enough. I am tired of
your sneaky tricks!
What tricks?
I don't know what your angle is,
but my kicking your
tail is all skill!
I call it cheating!
Heh. I don't care. All I know is
I don't use excuses
to cover up failure...
That's your way!
And again.
[grunts]
[gasps, growls]
Rapid Velocity Technique!
[yells]
[grunting]
[GOKU groaning]
[cackles]
[groans]
Goku falls unconscious
to the floor
like a rag doll after a
brutal beating by Tien!
Get up, Goku.
He wants to, but I don't think
he has a choice in the matter.
What?
[YAMCHA] Chiaotzu is using some
form of mental telepathy
to manipulate Goku's body.
[PUAR, OOLONG gasp]
Is that a fact?!
[ANNOUNCER]
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
--[TIEN] Was that 25 or 30 hits?
--Seven...
I lost count.
--I expected
--[ANNOUNCER] Eight...
more of a challenge.
--You're just as predictable as
--[ANNOUNCER] Nine...
my other opponents
and just as weak.
[GOKU]
Predictable?
Huh?!
[TIEN groans]
[CROWD cheers]
You'll regret that!
What?! Chiaotzu... Get ready.
You should've stayed down.
Do your worst, but I'll never
lose to a coward like you!
Oh really?! And just
how am I a coward?!
[yells]
[grunts]
Goku!
This injustice has
gone on long enough!
Huh?
[CROWD gasping]
[yells]
[growls]
All right, enough is enough!
This isn't going to be pretty.
[yells]
[grunts]
[CHIAOTZU]
Huh?
[LAUNCH]
Woah!
[LAUNCH groans]
[GOKU groans]
[BOTH gasp]
[groans]
Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] In what is becoming
an all-too-familiar pattern,
Goku has fallen to the floor
after a ferocious
beating by Tien.
You... cheated... me.
[gasps]
[SHEN cackles]
[SHEN thinking]
Good, Tien. Now finish him!
Wait... I wonder.
No, you have to get up, Goku!
[ANNOUNCER]
One... two... three...
[ROSHI]
Hm? Hm...
[SHEN thinking]
Strike! Kill him, Tien Shinhan.
You must do it now!
[TIEN thinking] Something isn't
right. This was too easy...
Chiaotzu! Is this your doing?
[TIEN thinking]
How dare you! This is my battle.
I did not ask for, nor do I
require your help. Set him free!
I-I'm sorry, Tien.
[SHEN thinking] Chiaotzu was
acting on my orders,
since you seem unable
to complete yours!
Every breath that child takes
is an insult to our house!
Or have you forgotten
your promise
to avenge the murder of Tao!?
[gasps]
[TIEN thinking] I will never
forget Tao, or my duty.
[TIEN thinking] I could
crush you where you lie...
End you right now
as you ended Tao...
Why should I bestow mercy
upon the merciless?
You've earned this!
[growls]
[SHEN thinking] Do it, Tien
Shinhan. Strike him down!
[growling]
[SHEN thinking]
Do it!
[growling]
Tien Shinhan!
Leave me alone!
[gasping]
Uh... that was kinda... wierd.
[ANNOUNCER]
What's this? Goku has recovered
and bounced back on his feet!
[BOTH gasp]
[PUAR, OOLONG sigh]
[KRILLIN laughs]
It's my turn now!
Goku, stop!
Ah!
He must die. I am your
master. Obey my command.
I have done as you asked...
I have defeated your
enemies and defended
the honor of our school.
The success of this match
is in my hands alone.
I do not need assistance.
Then prove it.
Destroy him at once!
No, I won't kill Goku. Doing so
would cause me to
lose this match.
Never mind the stupid match!
Make no mistake,
you are a killer!
Or do you forsake your destiny?!
No, Master... My destiny is not
what you'd have me believe...
I'm no killer.
[KRILLIN]
Oh...
Eh...
[SHEN growling]
You weak coward! Insolent fool!
You have allowed that senile
turtle hermit to warp your mind!
Uh, excuse me, but I can't
allow you to disrupt the f--
[SHEN] I'm speaking! I made you,
Tien! All that you are
has sprung from
my generous hands!
And now your insubordination
has clenched them into fists!
Now you'll pay!
Chiaotzu, paralyze them both!
Chiaotzu!
I'm sorry, Master. I will
do anything you ask of me...
But I cannot hurt Tien Shinhan.
[SHEN]
Come here!
[SHEN growling]
You dare defy me?!
[SHEN] So, the dissent spreads
throughout the ranks!
Then you, too, can
share in Tien's fate!
Chiaotzu!
Get back!
Ha!
[SHEN screams]
[CROWD shouting, gasping]
[TIEN]
Master Shen!
[ROSHI]
Don't worry about him.
That bird will be sore for
a while, but he won't perish.
There will be plenty of time
to discuss all of this later.
Let's get back to the fight!
Sorry. I guess I was
wrong about you cheating.
For once... I'm at
a loss for words.
I have absolutely no explanation
for what you just saw.
Let's just hope
Master Shen doesn't land
on anyone important.
Just kidding, folks.
I have forsaken my Master.
All that is left
for me now is this fight.
Let me make one thing clear.
This isn't about the rivalry
between our schools, or revenge.
I fight for one
purpose only: to win.
Never again will I be
led astray from my goal!
I'm glad. Let's get this
match back on track!
--[ROSHI laughs]
--[KRILLIN] Huh?
What's that all about?
I will win...
No matter how long...
...and no matter what
measures I have to take!
Okay. Let's go!
Whoa! Believe it or not,
it looks like
the fight has resumed!
[CROWD cheers]
[yells]
[groans]
[TIEN groaning]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[TIEN groans]
[GOKU]
Yaah!
[TIEN groans]
[CROWD cheers]
An unbelievable
counter-attack by Goku!
It looks like Tien is the
one eating floor this time!
One... two... three...
Tien recovers quickly
and it looks like
he's not too thrilled
with his opponent.
What's wrong? How come
you're not fighting back?
You didn't even
throw a single punch.
I've... paid my debt.
[GOKU]
What?
Chiaotzu's interference gave
me an unfair advantage.
Now we're even.
But, why wo--
[ROSHI]
A noble gesture.
Savor this moment,
because on my next attack,
I will fight full-strength,
and you will go down.
Come on, Tien. I know you
can do it! Let him have it!
[growls]
[growling]
Oh?
Eh? That's different.
[ANNOUNCER] Tien Shinhan is
attempting a difficult stunt...
I don't know what it is,
but it's definitely difficult.
[growling]
He... is going to stop
growing eventually, right?
[growling]
Yeah, the Four
Witches Technique.
This is gonna be great!
[yells]
[KRILLIN, ROSHI gasp]
[yelps]
[CROWD gasps]
Big trouble.
Big, big arms!
[NARRATOR] Goku had
difficulty fighting Tien
when he had two arms.
How will he combat four?!
The final showdown of the
22nd World Martial Arts
Tournament continues
with more action and surprises,
next time on Dragon Ball!