[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
the evil monster, Tambourine,
carried out his sinister mission
to seek out and
exterminate all members
of the Martial Arts Society.
[NARRATOR]
His master, King Piccolo,
created a new soldier,
Cymbal, for the sole purpose
of gathering the six
remaining Dragon Balls.
[NARRATOR]
While roaming the wilderness,
Goku stumbled upon a new
acquaintance, named Yajirobe.
The mountain boy
was displeased with Goku,
who mistakenly
ate his breakfast.
Both warriors quickly learned of
the other's incredible strength.
[YAJIROBE thinking]
This isn't going to be
as easy as I thought.
[GOKU thinking]
I kicked him as hard as I could!
Who is this guy?
[NARRATOR] Following the signal
of Yajirobe's Dragon Ball,
Cymbal made an appearance.
[NARRATOR] Which was cut short
by the mountain boy's blade.
[PICCOLO gasps]
No, no, no.
Cymbal has failed me.
[growls]
[GOKU]
Gee, that's a big fire.
What are you going to
do with that monster?
[YAJIROBE]
What do you think?
I'm gonna eat it, of course.
Late brektis.
Wh-What exactly do you
mean when you say brektis?
[YAJIROBE]
Lunch, dinner, brektis!
You're strange.
And they say I'm primitive.
But, you can't eat that.
It's not safe.
[sniffs]
Hmm... Delicious!
[GOKU]
Wait!
Hmm?
Eating monster
is a bad idea. Bad.
Eh. Well, don't
you worry about it.
This is my meal,
not yours, mine! So back off!
Tastes... like... chicken!
[GOKU]
Uh...
What is it?
Nothing. It's your stomach.
Yajirobe. That's your
name, right? Yajirobe?
Mmm... Yeah,
anything wrong with that?
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Cymbal. Cymbal, answer me.
Cymbal, I command you
to hear my call and respond.
Cymbal! Where are you?!
It's over.
Cymbal is no more. He's dead.
[chuckles awkwardly]
I sympathize with your loss.
He seemed like
such a nice beast.
Silence you fools!
How could your feeble,
inadequate brains possibly
comprehend how I feel?!
He was of my scales and blood!
[growls] I gave him life!
Watched him hatch
and spit his first slime!
Why you're, you're right!
I couldn't begin to understand.
Exactly! Cymbal
means nothing to us!
[growls]
[yawns]
Hey Pappa! You caught one!
Oh, it's a biggie!
[BABY BEAR] That's it Pappa!
You're doing it! You got him!
[BABY BEAR]
Ahh!
Hey, that's our fish!
[chuckles] If that
is true little bear,
what's it doing in my hand?
[BABY BEAR] Give it back!
Go and find your own food!
I have.
Monster!
Giran's back for
more food, Pappa!
Cover your eyes, son.
You can't just drop by
and steal peoples' things
whenever you
feel like it! Meanie!
[chuckles]
Who's going to
stop me? Your daddy?
When the fish runs out,
maybe I'll eat you,
and I'll make a
hat from you hide!
[chuckles]
Please, leave us alone.
Lights out!
[GIRAN] Huh?
Nobody touches my tail!
Are you Giran?
What if I am?
You die.
[GIRAN] Ah.
[GIRAN chuckles]
You are daring, and very stupid.
Ahh!
Huh... You fighters are
all the same, pathetic.
[TAMBOURINE]
Hmmm...
Big mistake!
[TAMBOURINE] It's you
who's made the mistake
of calling yourself a warrior.
[PANDA CUB] Can I open
my eyes now, Dad?
[PANDA POP] For a minute.
On second thought,
I think I'll keep them closed.
Good idea.
As a matter of fact,
I'll join you.
[BABY BEAR] It's just
like the stories Pappa!
A hero has come to save us!
Whoever you are,
you're making a big mistake.
This is my village to
terrorize. Go get your own!
Oh? Your ambition is limitless.
You dare mock me?
I'll rip you into pieces!
Is that the best you can do?
You give monsters a bad name.
Worse, you're way
out of your league.
[chuckles]
Well, ya never know,
I might surprise you.
Here, chew on this!
Huh?
Hmph. Thanks,
but it's not my color.
[laughs] That's
Merry-Go-Round Gum.
You can't move a muscle!
Oh, really?
Huh?
[gasps]
[laughs] It's sad
when plans fail.
You should have had a backup.
Anyway, it's time to die.
Congratulations.
No one's ever struck me
in a fight before.
I've really got
to hand it to you.
[TAMBOURINE]
I hope my eighth victim
is more amusing
than this wretch.
You saved us!
I'm appreciative beyond words.
By slaying Giran, you have
liberated our village!
Thank you so much!
Huh?
Pappa? Pappa, say something!
Now he is truly liberated.
[growls]
[TAMBOURINE]
Giran was just a job.
Your father, I killed for fun.
So we'll be fighting King
Piccolo and all of his minions
for control of the
Dragon Balls. Is that it?
[ROSHI] Mhmm.
And his possession of the four-
star ball puts him in the lead.
What we need is a plan
to knock him off his guard
long enough so that
we can steal the ball back.
Gotcha, I'd love to
knock him off his guard.
Careful, Tien.
I understand how you feel,
but King Piccolo is
a powerful adversary.
Maverick tactics
won't win this fight.
We must work together.
[TIEN growls]
Um, hey, the radar is blinking.
[ROSHI] It's a Dragon Ball...
200 kilometers
away heading south.
Changing course.
This one should be easy enough.
[TAMBOURINE]
Pity. I'd like one to last.
Ahhh. That was pretty good.
Nice and tasty.
But I need something else.
Don't worry. I'm sure
you'll have seconds.
Some more like this?
I don't think so.
This is the first one I've seen.
Not many creatures
of his size around here.
There's another.
He'll be after your
Dragon Ball, Yajirobe.
As long as you're wearing
that one, he'll come.
You brat!
That's Mr. Yajirobe
to you! Got it?!
I know what's going on here,
and I don't need your advice.
I don't mean to make you upset.
It's just that I've fought
this monster before.
I know what to expect.
Who said I'm upset?!
Do I look upset?!
[GOKU]
Ummmm...
I've been schooled
by many of the finest
hunters in the region.
I even graduated top of my clan.
Yep. Ya see, I'm what
you call phisisticated.
You're like Krillin,
but with a nose and hair.
Thanks, but I like my nose.
[YAJIROBE thinking]
Still, I could do without them.
Uh, maybe not.
This is nonsense!
You're distracting me!
I've got work.
There's a whole day's
hunting ahead of me,
and I don't have
time to waste on you.
It's about time
for you to leave.
Okay. Goodbye!
I'm not kidding Goku.
I never wanna see you again!
[GOKU]
Oh, there's one thing!
I once helped bring a
friend's father back to life.
There's a chance I may be able
to do the same for Krillin,
but I'd need the Dragon Balls,
like the one hanging
around your neck.
Can I have it?
You mean this
funny, little thing?
I don't understand.
Sure, it's nice and shiny,
but how is it supposed to help
you bring someone back to life?
[GOKU] The Dragon Balls
have special powers.
Yours is one of seven.
Once you have them all,
you get one wish.
[beeping]
This is the Dragon Ball
my precious Cymbal was
seeking when he disappeared.
That means the
one who possesses it
is responsible
for his destruction.
I want them to pay and
pay dearly for this insult!
Your Majesty,
while its true Cymbal's
whereabouts' are unknown,
it's impossible
that he was destroyed
by anyone inhabiting this world.
Here, we are invincible.
That's great news!
Maybe he decided to take in some
sights and lost track of time.
You know how kids are.
That's right.
Yes, maybe I was just dreaming
when I sensed his
life slipping away!
I am telepathically linked
with all my children.
I sensed his death.
[growls] Whoever ruined
my creation will suffer.
[TAMBOURINE]
This is strange. I must be lost.
Better slow down, champ.
Your leg hasn't
fully healed yet.
You don't want to spend
another month in bed, do you?
It is a bit sore.
At least we're safe out here.
King Piccolo and
his army would never think
to look for Yamcha
in this back wood palace.
That's true.
They have to search
an entire planet.
Besides, Master Roshi and the
others will be back soon enough.
Don't worry about Piccolo.
If he's dumb enough to show up,
I'll be glad to introduce
him to my lead army.
[TAMBOURINE]
Knock knock.
[ALL] Huh?
I'm lost. I'm seeking an island
nearby identified as NB18250012.
Oh, yeah, you're gonna want
to travel south, across the sea.
What a coincidence.
Huh?
That's where we lived
before we moved here.
Is that so?
Huh?
You're Yamcha!
[gasps]
[TAMBOURINE]
Hmmm... Scrawny and lame.
No, it's him, isn't it?
It's the monster!
[YAMCHA] That must make you
King Piccolo's "yes" man.
Yes. I mean, well,
you don't... Shut up!
Monster!
You're the one who
killed Krillin, aren't you?!
You are my next victim.
Eat lead, scaly!
[TAMBOURINE giggles]
That tickles!
[PUAR] They bounce right off!
So long!
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Tambourine!
We'll finish this later.
You coward!
[TAMBOURINE telepathically]
Master, everything
is proceeding as planned.
I have tracked down and
exterminated seven already.
I'm working on the eighth.
[PICCOLO telepathically]
That's good news.
I wish I had the same.
Unfortunately,
we have a problem.
Cymbal was sent
to retrieve a Dragon Ball.
Along the way, he was destroyed.
Destroyed?!
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Our response to this crime
must be swift and severe.
You are to abandon
your current assignment
and find the assailant.
I want an example made
of him. Do it slowly.
I will.
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Stay alert
and proceed to
coordinates WSC 2933.
Look, he's mumbling.
Do you think he's talking
to us or just resting again?
Perhaps he talks
in his sleep, sire.
[TAMBOURINE telepathically]
I'm on my way, Majesty.
I will not rest until this
vermin is brought to justice.
It's your lucky day.
Enjoy it. I will return soon.
Can't wait!
It's right here.
Unless this thing has
frostbite, we found it.
The ball must have found
a home in that iceberg
when it fell three
years ago. Just our luck.
Allow me, Master.
All right, be careful.
I just had these glasses fixed.
Hyaaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaaaaugh!
[ROSHI] Oh... Now
that's a lot of ice cubes.
But, uh, where's
the Dragon Ball?
Wait, there it is!
Looks like we're tied.
[laughs]
Uh...
Seems kinda small
to grant wishes,
even if there are seven of them.
What kinds of prize could
tiny little balls give you?
The Dragon Balls don't
actually give you the wish,
but the eternal Dragon
who watches over them does.
It's true. I promise.
Well, if I were you,
I'd ask for a bunch
of delicious food.
There's only one wish I have
and that is to
restore my friend's life.
And after that,
I'll destroy whatever that
thing is that killed Krillin!
[YAJIROBE] I thought
you only got one wish!
If you have more, you
should get your friend a nose.
[NARRATOR] Goku's wish
to confront Tambourine
is about to come true, without
any help from the Dragon Balls.
The monster is headed his way
and looking for a showdown,
next time on Dragon Ball!