[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
the Martial Arts Tournament
ended in tragedy
when Krillin was found slain
by a mysterious attacker.
Described as a monster,
the culprit stole
Goku's Four-Star Dragon Ball
and a list of members
of the Martial Arts Society.
Krillin didn't deserve this!
[NARRATOR] Enraged and consumed
by his thirst for revenge,
Goku left the others in search
of his friend's killer.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile,
Master Roshi uncovered
startling evidence,
which identified the murderous
fiend as King Piccolo,
a ruthless alien bent on
finding the Dragon Balls
and conquering the world.
Using the Dragon Radar,
Goku tracked down the killer
and rushed to attack.
[GOKU]
Stop!
[TAMBOURINE]
Hmm?
[GOKU growls]
Hey you, stop!
[growls]
A child? Explain.
[GOKU]
It was you!
You killed my friend!
Your point?
He was my best friend,
a great warrior!
His name was Krillin!
Krillin?
He fought you for the
Dragon Ball and you killed him!
Ah, yes. I have never seen
anyone so bald act so brave.
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
There's a big green monster
hanging from the ceiling!
This is the last time
I ever pull a double shift!
[KRILLIN growls]
Huh?!
[TAMBOURINE chuckles]
[KRILLIN thinking] Whatever
that thing is, it's fast.
[KRILLIN growls]
That's it? Pathetic.
You're not taking that ball!
Aaahh!
Where'd he go?! Huh?
[TAMBOURINE]
Up here!
Ahh! Somebody help me!
[chuckles] Dead.
Thanks for the update.
He was human. I did him a favor.
[GOKU]
What did you say?!
Taking his life
was a big mistake.
Nobody messes with my friends!
One thing I find tolerable
about your species, barely...
[slurp]
...is the sound you
make when you die.
What's wrong?
Did I make you cry?
Your bodies are
soft and fragile,
hardly suitable for fighting.
[TAMBOURINE]
But perfect for pain!
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
One kick, to the frontal lobe.
That's what killed him.
--[YAMCHA] Are you sure?
--[BULMA gasps]
Someone with Krillin's strength,
killed with one kick?!
It happens.
Krillin...
Ni-Ni-Nimbus.
[GOKU] Oof!
I'm tired.
I must have used up all of
my energy during the tournament.
[TAMBOURINE laughs]
If your muscles were
as tough as your talk,
this wouldn't be so boring.
[growls] I'll show you
how strong I can be!
Aaah!
[GOKU]
Hyaaaaa!
Auuh...
Really, what do you
hope to accomplish here,
other than to prove the fact
that your species
deserves extinction?
I don't know what you just said,
but I'm not here
to prove anything!
You're going to pay!
Haha! You are a conceited one.
I think someone should
take you down a notch.
Aahh!
The Flying Nimbus!
Power Pole Extend.
[TAMBOURINE laughs]
Ahhh...
[GOKU]Oof!
[TAMBOURINE laughs]
Unlike other life forms,
humans are worthless.
[TAMBOURINE]
They don't even make good pets.
Hmm?
You killed Krillin.
He was my best friend.
Right, got it.
I'm going to make you suffer.
Huh?
Ah. That solves that problem!
[TAMBOURINE]
I love my job. [laughs]
[BULMA] Please come back, Goku.
I can't lose you, too.
[BOTH]
Oh...
It's all my fault.
I should never have
given him the Dragon Radar.
[ROSHI]
Don't blame yourself.
Goku made his own
choices, as did Krillin.
There are no excuses.
It's just fate.
[BULMA]
You sound like you've given up.
I'm sorry, Goku's gone.
It's not true! Shame on you
for saying such a thing!
Why do you expect Goku to fail?
You should have more
faith in him than that!
That's right!
Mhmm. I agree
that there is a chance.
But now we have
to return to the island.
We must bury Krillin.
The rest can wait.
Grr. I didn't think
I could hate someone
I've never met before.
But King Piccolo is an animal!
Once I'm through with him, he'll
wish he'd stayed in that jar!
What's wrong with you?!
You sound like Goku!
This monster is too powerful.
You're just gonna
get yourself killed, too!
That list he took has
my name on it, Bulma!
And I'm not going to sit around
and wait for him to find me!
[gasps]
You're right! He's only
after people on the list.
I'm safe. No one ever
hunts pigs! We're cute!
No, you self-absorbed oinker,
you'll end up the main
course at his dinner table!
No one is safe.
King Piccolo's ambition
does not allow for bystanders.
Should he gain dominion over
our world, all will be lost.
[ROSHI] What his nightmarish
flames don't scorch,
his legions will devour.
[ROSHI] There will be
no quarter, no haven.
[ROSHI]
Complete genocide.
[laughs]
So this Evil Containment
Wave your old master
used to trap King Piccolo
the first time around
seems like
it worked pretty well.
Why don't we use it now?
Master Mutaito passed away
before he had a
chance to teach it to me.
Oh, I see.
Excuse me,
but it seems clear this is a
matter for the police to handle.
Yes, under normal circumstances.
But local law enforcement is ill
equipped to handle this crisis.
Uh, then who?
[ROSHI] It's up to us.
As Tien pointed out,
he's been defeated once.
He's not invincible.
If Goku comes this way,
tell him we've gone home.
I understand.
I think that if anyone
here can save us,
I strongly feel it's all of you.
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
[sniffles]
I took it for granted
he'd always be here.
[TIEN]
Master Roshi?
Hmm?
Chiaotzu and
I have talked it over
and we'd like to come
with you, if that's alright.
[ROSHI] Don't be silly.
Of course you can.
We'd appreciate your assistance.
Oh, I cannot believe
this is happening to me.
Suddenly my whole world's dark.
It's happening to
all of us, so stuff it!
Tiny... You're sure
it's a Dragon Ball?
Yes, it was exactly
where they said it would be.
Yes, I was right, you see. Do I
not offer invaluable counsel?
[PICCOLO]
Hmmm...
You've done well, Pilaf.
Once I have all
seven of these trinkets,
eternal youth will be mine.
Ah, ha ha ha ha!
Yes, soon we'll all
get what we deserve!
My full power will be restored
and I will once
again become invincible!
Uh, right, and your
looks will improve as well.
Heh heh heh.
[PICCOLO]
Hmm?
Which will be hard to imagine
considering how
good you look now!
You look great.
A model of beauty.
Uh, heh heh...
There's more. Here is the
list of names for participants
of the Martial Arts Tournament.
By all accounts,
it provides an accurate
record of every fighter
over the past 10 years.
Hmm... Good,
post them on the wall.
[TAMBOURINE]
As you wish.
You look tired. I'll take that.
[TAMBOURINE hums]
Ah hahahahaha!
I don't believe it. He's one
of their great fighters?
Hahahaha!
You know of this one?
Yes. And you won't be
needing his picture any longer.
I killed him during the mission.
Uh, Emperor. I think you
need to take a look at this.
[PILAF]
Hmmm...
Ah! No wonder the little
pest was so difficult to defeat.
He won second place
in the last two
World Martial Arts Competitions.
A worthy opponent for my skills.
Don't bother with
his picture either.
[gasps]
What? He was as
weak as the first one.
You killed Goku?!
If that was his name...
It was over so fast, there
wasn't time for introductions.
If the human I fought
won second place,
sir, these fighters will not
pose a significant challenge,
I can assure you.
Hmm... That may be.
Or they could still be
the same cunning warriors
that drove back my forces
and locked me in
a jar for decades!
We have to be absolutely sure.
Hunt them down, all of them!
Leave not one of them standing.
Yes.
And once you've
completed that mission,
find me the rest
of the Dragon Balls.
I'll take over the
world from there.
Hahahaha!
Remember, nothing fancy.
Just get the job done.
Now go, Tambourine.
Send those fighters
straight to oblivion,
and anyone else
who gets in your way.
Yes.
[whispering]
Emperor, I'm beginning to doubt
the wisdom of this alliance.
He seems unstable.
No matter how much
swampland he gives us,
I don't think this is worth it.
[martial art cries]
[FIGHTERS] We surrender!
We surrender!
Hmmm... That's all for today.
[TAMBOURINE]
Teach me!
[CHAPA]
Hm?
[TAMOBURINE laughs]
I'm here for my lesson.
Who are you, huh?
King Chapa is it true
you were once Champion of the
World Martial Arts Tournament?
[CHAPA] Yes.
What do you want of me?
[TAMBOURINE]
Die!
Huh?!
King Chapa!
I'm fine.
[FIGHTERS]
Huh?
Challenge accepted.
Ha! I'm not here to challenge.
I'm just going to kill you.
Ohhh!!
[CHAPA] Now let's see how
you fare against eight arms!
Eight arms. Is that it?
Here, try a hundred!
[FIGHTER A]
King Chapa! No!
Wake up! Is he unconscious?!
Oh...
I think he's...!
[sighs] Too easy!
[FIGHTER A]
Stop!
[TAMBOURINE]
Hmm?
So long as one
of us draws breath,
you will not escape
justice, creature!
[laughs]
If you insist. Who's next?
[TAMBOURINE cackles loudly]
[crowd cheering]
Reigning Champion Pamput
has knocked his opponent off
his feet and out of the ring!
This marks the Champ's
twentieth victory in a row!
Hahahaha!
I love your eyebrows!
[PAMPUT] Huh?
An uninvited guest has
dropped in on Pamput.
And by the looks of him,
I doubt he's friendly!
Hey you! Get down!
Now, you will die.
[laughs]
Listen, pal, for one thing,
get a better costume.
I can practically
see your zipper.
And get off my stage.
I'm the only star here!
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] Will Goku recover
from his horrible defeat?
Can anyone stop Tambourine
as he continues his assault
on unsuspecting fighters?
And who is his next target?
Find out all the answers
on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!