[ARALE]
Sembei, can you fix this?
[SEMBEI]
Sure. What is it?
It's a Dragon Radar.
A Dragon Radar?
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Arale brought Goku to see
Sembei Norimaki in hopes
that he could repair
the Dragon Radar.
However, General Blue
was also headed
for Sembei's house
to steal his airplane
and escape Penguin Village
with the stolen Dragon Balls.
Ah...
Do you think you can
fix it, Sembei?
Fix it? He'll make
it as good as new.
Sembei is an electronics genius.
Huh? Eh-hem.
There's nothing to
worry about, my boy.
Sembei Norimaki put the
possible in impossible.
Wow, how'd he do that?
[SEMBEI] Let's see now. This
little whatchamacallit is red.
That must mean
it's important. Yeah...
Definitely leave that in...
Okay, piece of cake.
[MAN]
This place looks a lot better
than it did on
the training video.
Look at those flowers!
We didn't come halfway
across the galaxy
to collect flowers.
Yeah!
Pardon me, sire, but it
looks like it's garbage.
Not garbage! Treasure, dummy!
Some fool was careless
enough to leave it behind
and if we didn't pick it up,
someone else would've!
Funny how their treasure
looks a lot like our trash.
Don't be ridiculous!
Who'd be dumb enough
to leave trash in the streets?
It appears, sire,
this treasure is empty.
Ah, what a strange
coincidence, so is your head!
Hurry, pick it up! This baby
could be worth a fortune!
[MAN]
Sire, yes!
One foot goes in front
of the other one!
Now come on, you nincompoop,
before we're discovered!
[MAN yelling]
[AKANE] I'm serious.
He flies on a cloud!
I saw it with my own eyes.
[TUN-TUK-TUN]
I'm sorry, Akane.
I'm sure the kid was
sitting on something,
but I doubt it was a cloud.
I'm telling the truth!
I know what I saw.
If you don't believe me,
why don't you go ask him?
His name is Goku.
Did I mention he knows karate?
I think someone's been
watching too much TV.
[TARO groans]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[TARO groans]
Taro! What--
Man! Who ran over you?
Th-They're here!
The Red Ribbon is...
I need some aspirin.
[SEMBEI grumbles]
Are you okay, Papa?
Yes, yes. Everything's
wonderful, son.
Goku, please tell me more
about the Dragon Balls.
There are seven
magic balls like this.
They have great power and
if you collect all of them,
you can ask for
one wish to come true.
[ARALE, GATCHANS cheer]
Hey, kids. Hungry?
Here are some snacks
to tide you over.
[GATCHANS cheer]
[ARALE] Oh!
[MIDORI] Here you go, Arale.
Gatchans, this is yours.
Goku, I've made some
fresh-baked cookies.
Have as many as you want.
Ah! Thank you!
[GATCHANS munching]
[SEMBEI] This isn't going to
work. It's just too complicated.
But how can I tell them that
without looking foolish?
[TURBO] Papa's in trouble.
I should help.
Huh?
You did it, Papa!
You fixed it! Congratulations.
Huh? I-I did? I mean,
of course, I did, yes.
What an incredible story!
I had no idea such
power even existed.
It's just so fabulous!
Tell me, Arale,
if you had the Dragon Balls,
what would you wish for?
I'd ask for a pony,
a sugar plum tree,
a rainbow that
never ends, and a flower
that changes color
every day. Oh, and--
Arale! Don't you remember?
I told you the Dragon Balls
will only give you one wish.
Aw... How come?
I don't know.
I guess that's just
the way they were made.
[SEMBEI]
I'm finished!
Really? Super!
[BLUE]
Ah. Home sweet home!
Hm. I guess I missed
the welcome wagon.
[BLUE laughs] Oh well,
I'll just have to settle
for the plane instead.
[ARALE] Wow! You did it,
Sembei! It's fixed!
[BLUE] What? The kid!
And the girl, too!
Why can't anything ever be easy?
For you.
Ah! Nice.
[SEMBEI]
I just hope it's really fixed.
[beeping]
It's working again!
It's great, Sembei. Thanks.
[GATCHANS, ARALE cheering]
[SEMBEI laughs]
Sembei, you are a genius!
What's this?
What's the matter?!
The radar shows there's
a Dragon Ball nearby.
[BLUE gasps]
[ARALE]
Look! I found one!
Surprise!
No, Dragon Balls are bigger.
Aw, really?
[beeping]
[GOKU]
Huh.
This way.
It's somewhere
over here. I think.
It shows the Dragon Ball
should be near here.
[BLUE growls]
[GAOS] All officers
not assigned to moving
the mayor's daughter
report for firearms.
This is our darkest hour!
[GAOS] Now I realize
some of you are nervous.
That's to be expected. But all
of us knew this day might come.
It is a difficult challenge,
but one we will face
with flying colors.
This is the moment
we've all read about.
Just remember.
Safety off, then fire.
Taro! What in blazes
are you doing?
He's here, captain!
[GAOS yelps]
Point that some place else!
Look out, they're coming!
Fire!
[TARO screams]
Captain, shouldn't we
wait to see the enemy
before we start shooting?
Hold your fire!
We're officers, not maniacs.
What was that?
I can't hear you
over the gunfire!
[GAOS whimpering]
You can stop shooting now.
I think he surrenders.
Where are they?
Hey captain, while we're
waiting for the enemy,
do you mind if we
break for lunch?
[GAOS growls]
Eh-hem. Excuse me,
captain, but we may want
to rethink our strategy,
just in case they're not
headed for the precinct.
Who needs strategy
when you've got bullets?
I wonder if it's not
too late to join the Army?
[beeping]
[GOKU]
Almost there.
[BLUE growls]
Doesn't he ever quit?
[GOKU]
Hm? Wow, that looks just like
Master Roshi's favorite chair.
[BLUE grunting]
There's no sign of a
Dragon Ball anywhere in here.
Let's keep looking.
[GOKU]
Let's try down here.
Whoa! Wait a minute.
[GOKU]
Down here. Huh?
[ARALE]
Huh?
[GOKU] The signal is
really strong in here.
Maybe it's in this box.
Huh?
[BLUE, GOKU scream]
[SEMBEI, MIDORI]
Huh?
[GOKU grunting]
[ARALE]
Huh?
He has Arale!
[GATCHANS gasp]
[ARALE gasps]
[GOKU growls]
[BLUE laughs] Looks like
you've made a new friend.
[GOKU growling]
You leave her alone!
[BLUE]
Easy.
[GOKU growls]
[BLUE] This knife is very sharp.
I'd hate for my hand to slip.
Let her go!
[BLUE chuckles]
[BLUE]
I don't like these odds.
If any of you so much
as moves a muscle,
the girl gets it, understand?
Listen, Mr. whoever you are,
I wouldn't do that if I
were you. It's a very bad idea.
[BLUE chuckles] I'm the only
one with the bad ideas
around here, friend.
And believe me, you don't
want me to use one.
No, that-that's not
what I meant--
[BLUE gasps] What's the
matter with you people?
[SEMBEI, GATCHANS gasp]
[BLUE whimpers]
Alright, you big bully!
Give me back my
Dragon Balls right now!
[BLUE gasps, growls]
What? What are you doing?
Huh.
[MIDORI gasps]
Goku! What did he do to you?
He froze my body again!
What?
He can't defend himself.
[GOKU grunting]
This is the
Penguin News Network!
We interrupt your program
for this important bulletin.
We're the first to bring
you this exclusive story!
We've just received information
that the Red Ribbon Army
is attacking Penguin Village!
With us now is Jay Daybe,
whose brother's best friend
knows someone who supposedly
thought about joining
the Red Ribbon Army once
and wrote a book about it.
Mr. Daybe, can you tell us
what you think may have caused
these notorious bandits--
Looks bad.
[PIGS scream]
[GOKU growls]
I can't move. Frozen...
Goku, calm down.
You're not making any sense.
There has to be an explanation.
Papa. That man has powers.
Oh.
Goku, is this man
a friend of yours?
He's a bad man.
He took my Dragon Balls.
[MIDORI gasps]
[BLUE laughs] You are a
glutton for punishment.
When will you ever learn that
there's nothing you possess
which I cannot take away.
Not even your
precious little radar!
Ugh. That's mi--
That's mine, give it back to me!
[SEMBEI] Excuse me, but that
really does belong to the boy.
You've been very
passive thus far.
Do yourself a favor and
don't mess it up now.
Oh, I'm in a hurry
so I'd better fly.
No problem, sir, but...
I haven't finished
the instruments yet.
[BLUE] Hm. Why do I feel like
I'm forgetting something?
[GOKU grunting]
Oh, that's right!
How silly of me.
I almost forgot the
most important thing of all.
[BLUE cackles]
[GOKU grunting]
I can't go away
without a goodbye fist!
[GOKU groans]
[SEMBEI gasps]
Oh, Goku!
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU grunting]
[BLUE cackles]
[BLUE grunts]
[SEMBEI gasps]
[BLUE cackles]
[GOKU grunting]
Why are you doing this?
Hm. Killing time
before my flight.
[GOKU grunting]
No!
[BLUE chuckles]
Die.
[SEMBEI yells] Arale!
Quick, it's playtime, honey!
Go show the bad man
how you play tag!
Ye-hey! Tag!
[BLUE laughing]
[ARALE giggling]
Huh? Oh no...
Tag! You're it!
[BLUE screams]
[GOKU groans]
[ARALE]
Yeah! That was a good one!
[ALL cheering]
[MIDORI sighs]
[ARALE giggling]
Now for the best part!
[BLUE yelping]
Jump and bump!
[BLUE groans]
[ARALE grunts]
[BLUE whimpers]
[BLUE groans]
[ARALE giggles]
I guess he didn't need
the plane after all.
[GATCHANS giggle]
[BLUE screams]
[GOKU grunting]
Huh? Ah... Hey, look!
I can move again!
[SEMBEI laughs]
[GOKU giggling]
Yeah!
[MAN screams]
[KING laughs]
Look at all my wealth!
[MAN]
Sire!
Police try'n to come in!
What?! The police?!
We've been discovered!
They're comin' to take
back my treasure!
Ready the ship.
We gotta get outta here!
[YAMADA] Listen partner,
if this goes down bad,
I want you to have my bike.
Gee, thanks. How many
payments are left on it?
[YAMADA]
What is that?!
[TARO, YAMADA groan]
[POLICE OFFICERS groan]
[KING cackles]
Let's see how they like this!
[POLICE OFFICERS scream]
[KING cackles]
So much for the big, bad police!
Yeah, we sure
showed them, didn't we?
[POLICE OFFICERS growl]
Let's fight!
Fire!
[POLICE OFFICERS grunting]
We're under attack,
abandon ship!
[YAMADA]
I hope they can swim!
[TARO] We did it!
[GAOS] Three cheers for victory!
[ALL]
Victory! Victory! Victory!
Well, sire, we still
have one another.
[KING yelps, gurgles]
Oh no! Sire! You must
use your feet in the water
if you want to paddle!
[ARALE giggling]
[ARALE] I'm here!
Good, you're well again!
Where is he?
I don't know. He hasn't
come down yet, silly.
Huh. He's still up in the sky?
I sure hope he took a snack.
You're one of the strongest
people I've ever met.
[ARALE giggles]
Thank you. But I'm nothing
compared to the Gatchans.
[GATCHANS coo]
Whoa!
That's incredible.
[GATCHANS]
Wah-hoo!
Oh, that was nothing, trust me.
They must be tired. You should
catch them on a good day!
I thought I was strong.
I never knew there was
so much I can't do.
I guess I need to
start training harder.
Hey! I almost forgot
about the Dragon Balls!
[GOKU]
Here they are!
Perfect!
Oh no! The Dragon Radar!
It's missing!
[GOKU]
He wasn't holding the radar.
So if it's not here...
It must still be in his pocket!
[GOKU grunts]
How am I going to
find him again?
I never should've
let him take it.
That guy still has
the radar and without it,
I can't get back home.
I'm stuck here.
Oh, don't be sad.
I can make you a
new one if you want.
You-You can? But how?
Papa, can I please have a few
parts off your airplane?
Sure, son.
But are you sure you can
make a Dragon Radar?
I saw the one you fixed.
That's a little more
than a few parts, son.
[ARALE giggles]
[GOKU] How does he do that?
[GOKU laughs]
Here.
[beeping]
Ah!
It's working!
[GOKU]
Thank you very much!
[TURBO]
You're welcome.
[SEMBEI laughs]
That's my boy, alright!
A genius just like his old man.
Flying Nimbus!
Thanks for everything
you've done for me.
You should think about joining
the martial arts tournament
next year. You'd be great!
[ARALE]
Hm?
[GOKU]
Goodbye!
See ya later!
[GOKU laughing]
[GATCHANS cheering]
[ARALE giggling]
[GOKU giggling]
Son, how about helping
me out with my airplane?
No, sir.
The Dragon Balls
are still at large.
[BLUE] I did, however,
manage to get his radar.
[STAFF OFFICER] You have
possession of the Dragon Radar?
It's in my hand as we speak.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Excellent.
Return to headquarters
immediately.
[BLUE]
Well... uh...
[STAFF OFFICER]
Is there a problem?
[BLUE]
Uh, no... well... um...
It's just that um...
It's kind of hard to explain...
It might take a while
to get back...
because I don't know where I am!
[NARRATOR]
It's been quite an adventure
for our young hero.
He leaves Penguin Village
with three Dragon Balls,
a new radar, and most
importantly, new friends.
Join us next time,
as Goku continues his quest,
only on Dragon Ball!