[PRIEST] Attention one and all!
It is with great pride and
pleasure that I welcome you
to the 22nd World
Martial Arts Tournament!
[NARRATOR] 182 of the
world's mightiest warriors
have converged upon this arena,
each possessing a
unique fighting style,
but sharing a common goal:
To crush his opponents
and seize the title
of Master of Martial Arts!
Will Goku prevail?
Let's find out!
May I have
everyone's attention?
Our first order of business
is to select the fighters
for each match.
To aid in this process,
each of you will draw lots
from the boxes
located on either side
of the service tables.
I'm 62. Looks like
they put me in...
...the latter half of block two.
I'm in the second
half of block one.
Please don't
put me against Goku...
Yeah! I got lucky!
I'm in block one,
but in the first half.
What about you, mister?
I drew number 178,
which, if I'm not mistaken,
puts me in block 4.
What luck!
We won't fight each other!
Ahem. Good.
We will now begin with
the Elimination Round,
which will decide the 8 fighters
who will advance
to the Championship.
Each match will be one-on-one
and confined to the
boundaries of the ring.
There is no time limit,
and each match will
continue until one opponent
is either defeated,
leaves the ring, or gives up.
No weapons are allowed.
In the event that an official
ruling is needed
to clarify a winner,
all decisions by the
tournament judges are final.
The tournament does not
take responsibility
for loss of
property or life.
As a reminder
to those outside the ring,
flash photography is strictly
prohibited. Thank you.
[neck cracking]
Well, this is it!
Good luck, Krillin!
Thanks!
That's the same kid, all right.
Are you sure? That's him?!
Oh, yeah.
Positive.
Die!
I didn't think we'd meet again.
Not here.
This is going to be
quite interesting.
Attention...
The first match in
the elimination round
will be held
in block number one.
At this time,
fighters number one and two
may enter the ring.
Here we go! Save my spot.
I'll be right back.
[GOKU] Get him, Yamcha!
The first match should
be starting about now.
I just hope they get
through it in one piece.
Don't worry, Bulma.
Yamcha and the others
will be just fine.
They know what
they're doing. Honest.
I sure hope you're right.
[neck cracking]
Say bye-bye.
[yelling]
Nice, but wood can't fight back.
If it could, it would have
a much better chance
of winning this match
than you do.
Gentlemen, please.
It's time to begin.
Let's focus on the match.
It's a shame some people
confuse technique with bravado.
This time, the turtle
will defeat the hawk.
So long!
Yah!
[GOKU gasps]
[AUDIENCE cheering]
Fighter one
wins by a knockout!
You did it!
You were incredible out there!
It was nothing.
What do you think? Tien?
Hey, Krillin's about
to start his match.
Let's go watch!
The second match
is about to begin.
Fighter number 63,
please step into the ring.
Huh?
[loud crashing]
What's that? An earthquake?!
[crashing continues]
He's huge!
[GIANT chuckling]
And who are
you supposed to be?
Uh, I'm your opponent.
Yeah? That's funny, you look
more like toe jam to me...
You're lucky I can see
the shine off your bald head.
Otherwise, you'd be
dust right now.
[GIANT laughing]
I remember who that giant is!
Yamcha, you know that guy?!
What is his name?
He's called Anton the Great.
He used to be the World
Professional Wrestling Champion.
Is he strong?
Mmm-hmm.
That's an understatement.
Anton is so tough
no one would fight him.
He left the professional circuit
and became an
underground fighter.
Fighters, now that
both of you are in the ring,
take your positions and begin.
I'm ready to begin now.
Care to make the first move?
The first move I make
will be your last, kid.
I doubt that.
When you squish,
don't forget to scream.
[GIANT laughing]
Come on, Krillin! Keep moving!
Don't let him get a hold of you!
[GIANT] Come to papa!
He's got Krillin!
[GIANT] Struggle all you want.
It won't make any difference.
No! Krillin doesn't
stand a chance!
That beast can crush
boulders with his bare hands.
Krillin!
How's my acting?
Before I became
a great fighter,
I considered
pursuing a career in acting.
You tricked me!
[GIANT yelling in pain]
Sir, what's the judgment?
Number 63 has left the ring,
which means 62 is the winner.
I'm the man.
[laughing]
[GOKU]
You did it! That was amazing!
You're definitely stronger
than you were three years ago.
Outstanding move.
Well thanks, guys, but relax.
This is just the beginning.
That was nothing. Just wait.
[TIEN laughing]
[TIEN] Your expectations
must be very low
if you consider that
an accomplishment.
Excuse me?
Wait. You are...
They're pupils of Hermit Crane,
which explains their rudeness.
He's a rival of Master Roshi's.
I remember them now.
Both of you are bad.
You tried to hurt
InoShikaCho and me!
You mean you've met
those two creeps before?
Amazing how events can change
according to one's perspective.
Actually, I did him a favor by
not finishing what he started.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm sorry,
I forgot my audience.
I'll use less syllables:
I can't be defeated.
You're lucky we don't have
a match in the preliminaries.
Whatever.
What's with your friend?
He's staring at me.
Midget.
You watch your mouth!
I wouldn't be talking
about anyone's height, Tiny!
Midget.
Stop saying that!
Chiaotzu, stop.
You know it it's not polite
to make fun of your inferiors,
especially when they
are as grossly inadequate
as these three.
None of them have
the slightest chance
of surviving the preliminaries,
let alone the tournament.
Get lost or get hit.
It's your choice.
Ha. Judging by your
last fight, I'm in no hurry.
You had the chance to deal your
opponent a critical blow
and you passed it up.
Big mistake.
Whenever I fight,
my objective is to defeat
my opponent, not murder him.
However, if you and I should
have a match in this tournament,
I'll be sure to
reconsider my policy.
Really? Why wait? Fight now.
Oh, anytime you're ready.
I'd welcome the
chance to shut you up.
[GOKU]
Yamcha, don't do this.
--[GOKU] Not now!
--It's okay, Goku.
This guy obviously
has a problem,
and I'm going
to solve it for him.
[ROSHI CHUN] Settle down, boys.
Whatever problem
you two are having,
you should ask yourselves
if this fight is worth it.
Because both of you will be
kicked out of the tournament.
Mind your business, old man.
That old man is Jackie Chun.
He won the last tournament.
[TIEN] And you fought at
that tournament, no doubt.
This just keeps
getting better...
If a decrepit old man proved
too great a challenge for you,
then you have no
business fighting me.
All right! Come on!
Thanks, but I don't
want to waste my time...
Enough, let's go.
[neck cracking]
What a jerk!
That creep doesn't know
who he's messing with.
My parents were six feet tall!
That Hermit Crane
is such a nuisance!
And I thought Roshi was bad!
So where did that imbecile
Turtle hermit run off to?
In the ocean.
Why don't you go
jump in and find him?
Knowing him,
he probably ran back home
too embarrassed to watch
his ill-advised pupils
get crushed in the tournament.
[chuckling]
Oh, be quiet!
It's common knowledge.
Roshi's boys can
be beat with one pinky.
You're misinformed.
Now, please, leave me alone. Go!
[CRANE] I can tell by your
posture that you're upset.
It's tough to back a loser.
Cheer up.
You don't have to
stay with Roshi's team...
I could use someone like you.
I can't believe
I'm listening to you.
You're wearing a crane!
What? What?
I can't believe
you're mocking me.
This happens to show
the status of my power!
Hey, lady!
Are you awake or what?
Ma'am? Hello?
[LAUNCH growls]
Can't a girl
get a moment's rest?
Give Master Roshi this message:
He can best help his pupils
by preparing for their funerals.
Attention all
competitors in Block Three.
Will fighters number 99
and 100 please come forward
at this time.
Good... my turn.
Fight well, Tien.
[TIEN] Of course.
[YAMCHA] Have you ever
met anyone more pompous?!
[KRILLIN] That jerk's all talk.
I bet he doesn't make it
through his first match.
No. That guy's a great fighter.
Yeah, right.
So you've already had a
run-in with this loser before.
Is he as strong
as he thinks he is?
Yes. He's tough.
What a show-off!
[loud crashing]
[SUMO] Invincible!
[laughing]
That's pathetic.
I'm surprised he
can even stand up.
I heard that!
Now say it again!
What's wrong? You must be deaf.
Try me.
Sure thing, tubby!
It's your funeral!
That sumo wrestler is strong.
Yes.
His extreme girth
is actually an asset...
Most attacks on him
are ineffective.
Fighters, hold your positions.
Ready, begin!
[SUMO] Invincible! Invincible!
[OFFICIAL C]
Fighter 100 is down.
Number 99 wins the match
by a knock-out!
What happened?
It was so fast I couldn't see.
I-I've never seen
anything like it.
That was four punches.
Correction, four
punches and three kicks.
His moves are so quick!
Sure. He may be fast,
but that doesn't mean
he's necessarily strong.
[TIEN thinking] These amateurs
are about to learn their place.
[OFFICIAL A] The next match
in Block One is at hand.
Numbers 27 and 28
please step forward.
All right! I'm up!
[GOKU] 1... 2... 3... 4...
[KRILLIN] Finally
we get to see Goku fight!
He should do well.
He almost won last time.
[ROSHI] Come on, boy.
Let's see how much you've
learned in the last three years.
Is that guy Goku's opponent?!
He doesn't look
very strong to me.
I don't envy him.
Goku's not someone you want
to fight in your first match.
The fighters get
younger every year.
Soon I'll be
fighting infants.
I know I've seen
that man somewhere before.
[CHEETAH] Ooh!
I don't believe it!
That's King Chapa, isn't it?!
You're right.
It is. King Chapa.
That's King Chapa?
The King Chapa?! Not good.
Goku doesn't know what
he's getting himself into.
What's the big deal?
[YAMCHA]
It's been said that he is
one of the
strongest men alive.
[ROSHI]
The last time he attended the
World Martial Arts Tournament,
he became the champion without
being touched
by a single opponent.
Goku's at a
severe disadvantage.
If Chapa is that good,
it's going to take a miracle for
Goku to stay alive out there,
let alone win the match!
Fighters, ready and begin!
Don't be afraid, little one.
I'll stop before I kill you.
Thank you.
[NARRATOR]
The tournament has just begun
and already Goku is up
against impossible odds.
Can he defeat King Chapa?
Find out on the next thrilling
episode of Dragon Ball!