[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragonball...
the 23rd World Martial Arts
Tournament reached
the final round where
Goku challenged Junior,
the newly hatched, reincarnation
of his old nemesis King Piccolo.
Both warriors were determined to
win the championship
at any cost, and attacked
with ferocious abandon.
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU, PICCOLO grunting]
[NARRATOR] It looked as though
Goku would dominate the fight,
until Junior turned the tables
and blasted the
unsuspecting hero.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[GOKU screams]
[ANNOUNCER whimpers, yells]
[NARRATOR]
When the smoke cleared,
Goku was found lying
face down in the dirt...
Junior watched with glee as the
announcer counted down
to Goku's dismissal.
For his opponent's defeat
ensured not only his revenge,
but his successful
domination of the planet!
No other warrior was strong
enough to stop Junior!
And so, the fate of the human
race rested in the hands
of an unconscious hero!
[CROWD whimpering]
[CHICHI gasps]
[ANNOUNCER]
He's down! Goku is down!
There is no movement in the pit!
One...
Two...
Three...
Those blasts, they...
they hit Goku straight on!
Please, wake up.
And four... Five... Six...
He's not waking up.
You're wasting time... Hurry.
R-Right.
He stopped...
What, is he just assuming
that Goku won't
recover from this?!
Poor Goku...
Hm, hm. Here lies...
humanity's hero.
Not very impressive.
He was hardly a challenge.
Huh?!
[GOKU chuckles]
Fooled you! Miss me?
[CROWD cheers]
[gasps]
[GOKU chuckles]
--[OOLONG gasps]
--He's alive!
[CHICHI laughs]
[GOKU grunts]
My uniform's cooked.
It feels like paper.
He made it...
We were worried for nothing.
I always knew he was hardheaded,
but he's got a
tough hide to boot.
There's not a scratch on him!
[CHICHI squeals]
That's it! Tear him up, Goku!
Show him who's boss!
You can do it!
Mop the floor with him!
Easy!
[whimpering]
Hah. Your lady friend seems
to think you can win...
She's going to be disappointed.
Oh yeah? Well, I'm still here.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR.] Only because
I allowed it... Hah!
Playtime is over!
[GOKU laughs]
Your ego is so bloated,
I'm surprised it
even fits in the ring...
I'm going to enjoy taking you
down a notch or two.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Why don't you do us all a favor
and leave the one-liners to me?
My pleasure.
That's it. Keep Junior
babbling so you can rest.
Yes. Quite clever.
Here's an idea. Why don't you
stop talking so we can fight?
[GOKU growls]
You should be careful
what you ask for.
I hope Goku knows what he's
doing. Junior's tricky.
[PICCOLO JR. snarls]
[laughs]
Huh...?
Ahh... Ahh!
[sighs]
[whimpers]
[GOKU growling]
[PICCOLO JR. growling]
[GOKU growls]
[BOTH growling]
[growling continues]
[whimpering]
[yelling]
[GOKU growls, yells]
[BOTH yelling]
[GOKU, PICCOLO growling]
--[PICCOLO yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
[BOTH growling]
[whimpers]
[growling continues]
[yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Whoa! After an amazing attack,
Goku has vanished again!
[ROSHI] Ahh... He's
disappeared without a trace.
Junior won't stand a chance if
Goku can keep him guessing.
Goku is excellent at vanishing.
I sure don't envy
Junior right now.
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[gasping]
[laughs]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Goku?!
Ah, is he...?
[laughs]
Goku, no!
He's... gone again!
[gasps]
Where is he?!
I'm back here!
--[GOKU growls]
--[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
That's it... Punch him!
Yeah!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
That was one big mistake, human!
Yeah, heard that before!
Up until now, I've tolerated
your insolent behavior!
But no longer!
[snarls]
Now! You must pay!
You just sealed
the fate of your race!
[screams]
[GOKU growls]
[gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs, growls]
Stop it! This is between
you and me, Junior!
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[GOKU]
Everyone... Get down!
[ROSHI gasps]
What's wrong!?
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Watch as your precious people
are crushed under the weight
of my blast!
Leave them alone!
It's me you want!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Get down here, you coward!
[growls]
[GOKU]
Here I am!
Come on! Look into
the eyes of your killer!
That's right, fire at me!
Hyyaah!
[yells]
[screaming]
[whimpering]
[CROWD gasping, screaming]
[whimpers]
[whimpering]
Look! The mountains!
They're--They're gone!
[growls]
Why won't he just die?!
[CROWD cheers]
[GOKU]
This is getting way out of hand!
[ROSHI grunts]
Those cheers are well deserved.
If Goku hadn't drawn his fire,
none of us would
be here right now.
Master, I don't feel so good...
Heh!
That was but a mere
glimpse of my power.
I can destroy you
at any time if I wish!
Fine... Here's a surprise
from me to you...
Super Kamehameha!
What?!
Ka... Me...
A Super...
...Kamehameha Wave?!
[GOKU]
Ha... Me...
A Super Wave?
What is he talking about?!
[GOKU growls]
[ROSHI]
Goku, wait! Don't do it!
Huh?
Think about it... Don't forget!
If you use that wave, not only
will you destroy Junior,
but Kami, too!
[GOKU growls]
Yeah... You're right...
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR.]
Aww, too bad.
But I'm sure Kami thanks you,
from the bottom of my heart!
I'll... stop you!
[chuckles]
I know that you will try
your best, Goku...
That's why I'll enjoy
watching you fail!
Be honest, at times like this,
you wish you were the bad guy!
[GOKU growls]
Fool... I am unstoppable!
There is nothing you can do,
not without jeopardizing your
precious Kami! I've already
won this battle!
What a loser!
Big time!
♪ He's scared of Goku. ♪
[BULMA, PUAR, OOLONG]
Huh...?
You stand there, so defiant.
But I've seen your heart.
It bleeds for these weaklings
who call you "hero."
You're just as
spineless as they are!
Rrgh! Then come down!
Huh?
Calm... Stay calm...
You don't get it...
I am the superior being here.
I call the shots!
I am the future!
With one fell swoop, I can rid
this world of your kind!
I shall usher in a new age,
the age of oblivion!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Leave these people alone!
You don't need to waste your
time on them if you're so tough!
Come get me!
They will all die!
[GOKU growls]
Maybe we should get out of here.
No. I think this is
all part of the show.
[yells]
[PICCOLO JR. growling]
[yelling]
Oh, no! That energy!
Watch out, Goku!
[gasps]
[GOKU thinking]
What am I gonna do now?!
Well... it was fun
while it lasted.
Goku will stop him, I hope!
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[PICCOLO JR. laughing]
[whimpering]
[MAN screams]
[screaming, shouting]
[growls]
Ready?!
This is the end!
[GOKU growls]
Hey, wait...
The Dragon Balls!
Goku, it's okay!
You can kill Kami!
[gasps]
Even if you destroyed Junior,
we can bring back Kami
with the Dragon Balls!
Restore his life,
like you did for me!
[gasps]
Yeah, right!
Why didn't
I think of that?!
Go ahead! Super Kamehameha
that creep all you want to!
Yeah! Thanks, Krillin!
[GOKU growls]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
Get ready for a Kamehameha
Wave, super style!
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
[PICCOLO JR.] Ha! Aren't you
forgetting something?!
You need the Eternal Dragon
to make a wish come true!
And he was destroyed
three years ago!
You're right, Junior!
But the Dragon was resurrected!
Haaah!
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
Raaugh!
[PICCOLO JR.] How is this
possible? I'm invincible!
[screaming]
[PICCOLO JR. screams]
[NARRATOR] With devastating
fury,
the Super Kamehameha Wave
enveloped Junior.
Has Goku finally
achieved victory?!
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!