[NARRATOR] The sun brightens
on a new day in Suno's village.
Joy fills every home as
the villagers celebrate
the safe return of their chief.
At Suno's house, Goku enjoys
a much-deserved break
from his adventures by
doing what he loves most.
[GOKU slurps and smacks]
My, someone's hungry
this morning.
[GOKU] Mmm!
[GOKU slurps and smacks]
Eww...
[GOKU slurps]
Aaahhh...
That sure was great!
Goku!
Eat all you want, son.
Because of you,
our village is whole again.
Mother, bring Goku
another casserole.
[NUMBER 8 chuckles]
In all the commotion,
I forgot to ask you
if you ever found that ball
you were looking for, sweetie.
That's right.
No one ever found
the Dragon Ball.
We searched everywhere for it,
but nothing ever turned up.
It was probably
never here at all.
Or so I guess.
Wait.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Speak up.
What's wrong, Eighter?
I have it with me.
[GOKU gasps]
Here it is.
[GOKU] The two-star ball!
You found it, Eighter!
[SUNO'S DAD] Are you telling me
the Red Ribbon Army
had the Dragon Ball
the whole time?
I found the ball inside an
ice cave, near Muscle Tower.
I was going to give
it to General White,
but then I learned
he was planning
to kill all of the villagers
once he had recovered it.
I couldn't bear the
thought of being responsible
for something like that,
so I kept it hidden.
You, my friend,
are a true hero.
That cinches it then...
You're welcome to
live in our village.
Me? And Goku, too?
Of course!
You're both honorary
members of this village.
You can stay here
as long as you want.
[SUNO giggles]
Thank you,
but I can't stay.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Why not?
This one's nice, but I'm
looking for the four-star ball.
That's the one
my Grandpa gave to me.
It's the only one I care about.
I see...
Eighter, you're welcome to live
at my house if you'd like.
Huh? With you?
Wow that's great,
isn't it?
Just think, now you'll have
real friends and a real house!
Yes...
Then it's settled!
But I'm not really human.
I've met people
I wouldn't call human.
It's your heart that counts,
and you've got a big one.
That's nice...
You are all so kind to me.
[SUNO'S DAD] This is fantastic.
I know the other villagers will
be just as excited as we are.
[SUNO] You'll love it here!
[NUMBER 8] I must go...
[SUNO] Aww...
Thank you.
I appreciate the offer...
but I can't live with you.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Why not?
There's a bomb planted
somewhere inside my body.
[VILLAGE CHIEF gasps]
A bomb?
I remember.
All right!
Now get started...
Take care of this nuisance!
I can't
Huh?!
Yes, excuse me, but I...
I hate violence.
We planned for an
incidence just like this.
A surprise was implanted in
your body when you were built.
Let's call it
obedience insurance.
All I have to do is
press this big red button
one time and then BOOM!
The bomb inside you detonates!
Oh! That's unimaginable.
There's no way of knowing
when it will explode.
Why would anyone
do such a thing?!
I'm so sorry...
I can't stay here.
I would be putting
everyone's life in danger.
No. It doesn't have
to be this way, Eighter.
Huh?
I know someone
who can help...
His name is Dr. Flappe.
That's right! He can save you.
Dr. Flappe is a genius!
Dr. Flappe?
So, who is he?
He is an
extraordinary scientist.
He lives alone in the
mountains behind the village.
He built a laboratory up there
so he can work on his
experiments undisturbed.
You could ask the doctor
if he would remove
the bomb from your body!
The problem is he
doesn't care much for people.
If he doesn't like you,
he won't even talk to you.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Hmm...
Dr. Flappe loves me.
I've been to his
house several times.
I bet he'd talk to Eighter
if I were there.
That's true.
The doctor is
rather fond of Suno.
If she goes along, he might be
inclined to help Eighter out.
Will you go with
him, sweet pea?
[SUNO] Mm-hmm!
Hey! I'll go too!
Then it's settled!
You kids will leave
first thing tomorrow.
Thank you for being
so kind to me...
[MURASAKI grunts]
[MURASAKI growls]
[SUNO] Oooh!
You can have them
if you want.
Are you kidding?
And have the Red Ribbon
Army after me? No thanks.
They're your balls...
You keep them.
Okay. Suit yourself.
Goku, is that the radar
General White was trying
to steal from you?
Yep, it sure is!
It was a present
from my friend Bulma.
See, you just
push this button...
What the-- Hey!
What's the matter?
I don't know.
I-It doesn't seem to be working.
I guess I must've broken it
while I was fighting.
If the doctor can help Eighter,
maybe he can also fix
your gadget too!
Oh... that's a great idea!
Do you have the food I packed?
[SUNO] Yes, Mother.
Soon you'll be good
as new, my boy!
[NUMBER 8 chuckles]
[VILLAGE cheers]
[GROUP] Goodbye, see ya!
Thank you so much, bye!
See that big mountain up ahead?
The doctor lives
right behind it.
It sure is a long journey.
I hope he's willing to help.
He's a very nice person
once you get to know him.
I guess it won't
hurt us to ask.
The worst thing
he can do is say no.
Come on, guys.
There's nothing to worry about.
Dr. Flappe is a sweet old man.
He's up there all day creating
all sorts of wonderful stuff
you wouldn't believe.
[GOKU &amp; NUMBER 8] Hmmm...
I hope you're right, Suno.
Where do you
think you're going?
[GOKU] Huh?
Wait!
[MURASAKI gasps]
I don't think we should watch.
[GOKU sighs]
[GOKU hums]
[MURASAKI growls]
You'll pay for that,
you dispicable runt!
[GOKU] Wow! What a shiny pond.
You're standing on the water!
Of course. The water is frozen.
What kind of water is that?
The water became hard in the
cold temperature, that's all.
Whatcha waitin' for, silly?
Let's go!
All right! I'm in.
Here goes nothing!
[GOKU shouts]
That was funny!
--[SUNO laughs]
--Oh yeah! That was great!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU shouts]
[SUNO giggles]
Come on, Eighter!
Join the fun!
Wow! This hard pond is great!
Who knew water could do
so many neat things?
We have to come back
and do this again!
What a moron.
It doesn't take a
ninja to walk on ice.
[MURASAKI yells]
[ALL] Huh?
[MURASAKI] Oh!
[MURASAKI] Great!
Would you just leave already?!
Did you hear that?
I could have sworn
I heard a splash.
Me too... very strange.
[MURASAKI] Ho-ho.
This is nothing...
[GOKU] Hmm...
[MURASAKI] Ohh...
he's talking too much...
Well, I don't hear anything.
I guess not.
[MURASAKI] Ugh, I always
knew I'd die an ironic death!
Come on, we'd better go.
Yeah.
[MURASAKI] I can't
take it anymore!
I need air! Can't breathe!
Where's the hole?!
Where's the stupid hole?!
Open up, ice!
[MURASAKI]
Dang, this ice is hard...
I hate that kid!
[MURASAKI growls]
[MURASAKI gasps]
Look! We made it!
Let's go!
[ALL laugh]
[ALL] Huh?
[MURASAKI (BEAR)]
Oh, how'd they see me?!
[GOKU] It's a bear!
[MURASAKI (BEAR)]
Hm! Uh, just a bear!
Come on!
[NUMBER 8] Hah. Bear...
[MURASAKI (BEAR)] A circus bear!
[MURASAKI (BEAR) grunts]
[ALL] Huh?
[MURASAKI (BEAR) yells]
[MURASAKI grunts]
[MURASAKI (BEAR)]
I am a bear covered with snow...
Curses!
[SUNO] Wait here.
Let me see if he's home.
[SUNO] Hello? Dr.
Flappe, are you home?
--[engine whirring]
--Maybe he's gone.
Private property!
Doctor!
[DR. FLAPPE laughs] Suno!
[DR. FLAPPE] So,
ze two of you took on
ze entire Red Ribbon Army, huh?
That's right.
They're both very strong.
No, no. Not me.
I'm really not that strong.
Oh, yes you are.
Stop joking around.
Remember how you
tore down Muscle Tower?
[NUMBER 8 chuckles]
Anyvay, I'm glad ze
village eez at peace again.
I hope the Red Ribbon
Army never returns.
Me, too.
[SUNO] Did the army do anything
to you while they were here?
Ahh?! No, no, I never saw
a trace of ze army up here.
They do not, uh, like it.
It is too cold.
You're lucky. Can you
believe those mean men
actually put a bomb
in Eighter's body?
Hmm...
You can take it out,
can't you?
You can save Eighter!
Dr. Flappe!
[DR. FLAPPE gasps]
You can take out
his bomb, right?
Uh... Yes, yes, of
course. Absolutely.
Don't give it a second thought.
Thank you, Dr. Flappe!
That's great!
[NUMBER 8 chuckles]
Isn't it, Goku?
[GOKU snores]
Poor boy must
be exhausted.
He'll sleep better with
a pillow and blanket.
I'll be right back.
[MURASAKI] It's been
a long time...
Murasaki!
Please, leave me alone!
[MURASAKI grunts]
[MURASAKI]
What's the matter, Doc?
Aren't you happy to see me?
[MURASAKI chuckles]
We have a little
business to discuss.
I told General White
I'm out for good!
Whatever deal you made
with the good General
went out the window with him.
He and his soldiers were
defeated yesterday
after Android No. 8
went renegade.
You remember that one, right?
--[DR. FLAPPE whines]
--Of course you do.
After all, you made him.
[MURASAKI] Just think, Doctor,
how all your fellow villagers
might react if they learned
of your involvement
with the Red Ribbon Army.
That you were the man
responsible for giving life
to their most
monstrous creation!
[NUMBER 8 growls]
[DR. FLAPPE gasps]
[MURASAKI chuckles]
If word gets out, there won't
be a mountain high enough
to keep you safe.
Just tell me what
you want me to do!
The brat sleeping in your living
room has the Dragon Ball.
I want you to get it for me.
After that, all you have to do
is take care of the boy...
permanently.
[DR. FLAPPE growls]
No! I vill not do that! Never!
[MURASAKI] Are you sure?
I could have gone
back to the village
and gotten a blanket
faster than this.
Just like you, doctor,
I'm about to lose my patience.
Hello?
--Suno! Run, run, dear!
--[SUNO screams]
[MURASAKI] Come here!
[SUNO screams]
I'll make this simple.
Do as I say,
or the girl gets it.
I understand!
[GOKU snores]
[NUMBER 8 snores]
Doctor?
What are you doing
with his Dragon Balls?
--[DR. FLAPPE wails]
--Wait! Stop!
Is it lunchtime?
[MURASAKI giggles]
At last it's mine!
[SUNO shrieks]
That's Suno! She's in trouble!
[ALL gasp]
Sergeant Murasaki!
[MURASAKI laughs]
So long, losers!
Who went out the window?
It was Murasaki, and he took
your Dragon Balls with him.
What?!
[MURASAKI laughs]
[GOKU] Stop! Thief!
Just like old times,
hey, little brat?!
Come on! Eat snow!
Hey! Come back!
[GOKU] Stop!
Give me back my stuff!
[GOKU] Wait!
So long, shorty!
Ka-Me-Ha-Me-...
Haaa!
[MURASAKI gasps]
[MURASAKI screams]
[screaming continues]
Oh, thank goodness it's here!
I was afraid he
would eat my lunch!
Somehow, I always thought
Dragon Balls were bigger.
[BOTH] Hmm...
I did it. Zere's nothing
more to worry about.
[BOTH giggle]
--Yeah!
--All right!
[DR. FLAPPE sighs]
[gasping]
Quick hands.
[NUMBER 8]
I owe you my life, Doctor.
Thank you.
--[GOKU] Thank you!
--[SUNO] Thanks, Doctor!
Yes, yes. You're welcome.
But there's one little thing...
Your radar is too sophisticated
for me to handle.
I... couldn't fix it.
That's okay.
I'll just take it back to Bulma.
She'll know what
to do with it...
Wha...?
[ALL scream]
The bomb!
--So long, Bye-bye!
--Take care, Dr. Flappe.
Bye!
Good luck, my friends!
[DR: FLAPPE] I wish
I had ze courage
to tell 8 that
I planted ze bomb.
I had no choice.
Zey would have killed ze
villagers if I didn't.
[ALL] Bye!
[DR. FLAPPE] Perhaps some day
I can tell him ze truth...
[MURASAKI gasps]
Like the ebb and
flow of the tides,
my wrath shall
remain constant...
I'll have my revenge!
[MURASAKI screams]
[NARRATOR] It's always nice
to end a story with a bang.
Join us next time for
another exciting adventure
on Dragon Ball!