[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
After dethroning King Furry
on international television,
Piccolo announced his intentions
for his new regime of freedom.
And when King Piccolo
speaks of freedom,
he's not kidding around.
[PICCOLO] Robbery, violence,
murder, and war...
All will be welcome in
my glorious new kingdom.
We will establish a
worldwide order of evil,
and destroy outmoded
ideas of justice.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Goku
finds the Ultra-Devine Water
and drinks the sacred liquid
fabled to give great strength
to those who survive its poison.
[NARRATOR] But are his efforts
rewarded with power?
[NARRATOR]
Or death?
[GOKU]
W-What happened?
[YAJIROBI] You did it, Goku!
You survived! You survived!
So, do you feel
any stronger, Goku?
I don't know.
I do feel different,
but I just can't explain it.
[YAJIROBI] Well, it sure
didn't change your looks.
You're still just a
goofy-looking kid with a tail.
[YAJIROBI]
Huh?
[DARKNESS groans]
Thank you, sir!
[GOKU]
Let's go!
It's time!
It's time? Time for what?
We don't know the
way out of here.
I do. It's so clear.
Grab hold now.
We're leaving, Yajirobi!
I'm coming, Piccolo!
[yells]
[YAJIROBI yelps]
My first decree is to
abolish the police
and release all criminals!
I want riots!
Order is legally dead!
[WOMAN]
Get in the house!
Well, what are you
waiting for? Let it begin.
[PICCOLO cackling]
[CROWD screaming]
[horn blares]
[MAN]
Long live King Piccolo!
Please, return to your homes!
Piccolo is not
the official ruler!
And all those who break the law
will be punished accordingly!
--[POLICE MAN yelps]
--[BEAR yells]
I'll keep it under advisement!
[POLICE whimpering]
[CROWD yelling]
Come on. Give it up, warden.
Get comfortable. You're not
goin' anywhere, Johnny.
At least not on my watch. So,
just sit back and relax there.
Oh, I'm fine right here.
[CROWD screams]
[PICCOLO cackles]
Well, sir, this is about
as far as I can take you.
This is fine. Thank you.
You be careful out there.
There's some strange things
going on in the world today.
[NUMBER 8]
Huh?
Oh, Suno... Be alive.
[PICCOLO cackles]
[BOTH gasp]
--[MAN yelps]
--[cackling continues]
[TIEN growling]
Piccolo!
[ALL sigh]
So, that's it, huh?
I guess it's all completely
hopeless now. I give up.
Yeah? Well, I'm not a quitter.
There's still hope in Tien.
And his Evil Containment Wave!
Hold on.
[YAMCHA] Remember what
Master Mutaito said?
Anyone who uses the wave...
...will die.
[engine revs]
[GOGGLES laughs]
Great time to be alive, huh?
How you spell, uh, annihilation?
Huh? Uh...
Hey! This ain't no
spellin' bee! Don't bug me!
[HOG]
Let's see. Umm...
Close enough. Yeah.
[NUMBER 8]
Suno!
[gasps] Huh?
Eighter! Yay!
It is you. I'm so happy now.
Well, I'm not happy.
Hardly anyone survived, and the
ones that did aren't doing well.
I'm afraid I'm not much good.
Did you send for help?
[SUNO]
Most people just left us.
[NUMBER 8 gasps]
You have to believe
I tried my best.
[high-pitched music plays]
[SUNO, NUMBER 8]
Huh?
[high-pitched music plays]
[tires screech]
Come on. Let's roll.
There's nothing here.
She's right, man.
The place is trashed.
Keep on lookin'.
There might be a fireproof safe
or somethin'. You never know.
[NUMBER 8]
Hey! Over here!
Please, you must help.
Many people are hurt.
Oh, yes! You could take them to
a hospital on your motorcycles!
They need you!
Won't you help us?
Ha! You kiddin' me?
Oh, man, get real.
[HOG] They don't know
who they're dealin' with.
[laughs]
They're about to.
Dude! You have
the great pleasure
of running into loyal followers
of King Piccolo's Tribe of Evil!
The great one doesn't
want us helping people!
Uh, no offense!
Piccolo makes good speeches, but
I'm pretty persuasive, myself.
[GROUP cackles]
[SPIKE]
Rumble!
[yelps]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[yelps]
[GROUP screams]
[growls]
Great speech. I'm convinced!
[SUNO laughs]
[grunting]
[yells]
[panting]
[groans]
[TIEN]
I've done it. I've mastered it.
Hey! Slow down!
Well, come on! We've got
to hurry now, Yajirobi!
[GOKU]
I see it!
Please, be the door!
Hey! Master Korin!
[KORIN]
That you, Goku?
[laughs]
Yeah, it's me!
He didn't die after all.
His power is very impressive.
Could you let us out, please?
Yeah. It smells bad
down here, and I'm hungry!
Okay! Hold your horses!
[yelping]
[groans]
Welcome back.
[growls]
I'm coming for you, Piccolo.
[YAMCHA]
Tien Shinhan? Come in, Tien.
This is Yamcha. Are you there?
Come in, Tien!
This is Tien Shinhan.
[YAMCHA]
Hey, I...
Tien, where are you?
[TIEN] I'm off to present
a special gift
for our new King's coronation.
Then, that means...
[TIEN] Yes, I've mastered
the Evil Containment Wave.
It's time to put
it to the test.
I'm proud of you,
Tien, so proud.
[TIEN]
Don't be.
This is not about me or rather,
this is about the
bad things in my life
that made me no better
than King Piccolo.
This is about atonement,
and I only hope it's enough.
Goodbye, my friends.
Goodbye, Tien!
Farewell, Tien Shinhan.
You're the bravest.
I sense it. I feel it.
I'm not what I was before,
and it's not just
the strength, either.
I feel power and at peace...
with... with everything.
[KORIN thinking]
I suspected he would survive,
but I didn't consider
what it would mean.
Could he truly be the one?
Are you sure?
You sure look the same.
And there's something else...
[gasps]
What's he doing?
[GOKU]
I know where Piccolo is.
And how do you know that, Goku?
Well, I don't know
what to call it.
I guess you could say
I sense his power level.
Mm-hm. That is exactly
what you're sensing!
Feel strong?
[GOKU]
Mm-hm!
It's gift time!
Wha...?
Flying Nimbus!
Nimbus?
[laughs]
What is that?!
[yelps]
Jump in there and pick out
a good one, Goku.
I thought the Flying Nimbus
Master Roshi gave me
was the only one in existence!
Nah, that was just an old model
I gave him years ago.
--[GOKU laughs]
--[YAJIROBI yelps]
[sobs]
[GOKU grunts]
Master, I like this one!
[KORIN]
Nice choice, Goku!
Yeah!
[GOKU laughing]
Do you wanna go for
a ride, Yajirobi?
What? No way, Goku!
I like living too much!
Oh, well. I guess I'll
see you later, then.
[GOKU] Thank you for the
new Nimbus, Master Korin!
[KORIN]
So, where're you goin' now?
To Piccolo.
Come on, my new Nimbus.
Let's go!
Yeah!
[GOKU laughing]
Wow! That's fast! I want one!
[KORIN]
It's fast, but you have to have
a pure spirit to ride one.
[YAJIROBI] Well, then give
me one, Master Korin!
[KORIN]
Did you even hear me?!
The trial of the Ultra
Divine Water is over,
and Goku passed with
flying colors!
[NARRATOR] Now, armed with
greater powers and a new Nimbus,
Goku feels up to the challenge
of facing Piccolo again.
[NARRATOR] But Tien has a
head start and is willing
to sacrifice himself
to defeat Piccolo.
[NARRATOR] Will Goku make it
in time to beat Piccolo
and stop Tien from
needlessly giving his life?
[PICCOLO cackles]
[NARRATOR]
Find out on the next
thrilling episode
of Dragon Ball!