[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Tien Shinhan used the
Evil Containment Wave
against King Piccolo.
Unfortunately, Tien's
plan to trap Piccolo
blew up in his face.
Once again, the battle seemed
to shift in Piccolo's favor.
Tien's misfire left him
drained of all energy
and vulnerable to attack...
It appeared as though the
brave warrior was done for.
[gasping]
[TIEN groans]
[PICCOLO]
Make it as painful as possible.
[DRUM chuckes]
[NARRATOR] Until, from out
of nowhere, help arrived.
--[PICCOLO] That's impossible!
--[PIANO gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Goku returned for a rematch!
[TIEN]
Goku! Get out of there!
[DRUM]
You're not goin' anywhere runt!
No one treats me like that
and gets away with it!
Exactly... Teach these fools a
lesson they won't forget!
[laughs]
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR]
Piccolo quickly realized
that this time, Goku
wasn't kidding around.
[NEWSCASTER] We are sending
you this broadcast
at great risk to
our own lives but,
as always, we're
committed to getting you
all the latest news
fast and first!
You're seeing live shots
from West City,
which King Piccolo
vowed to demolish!
A shockwave of panic
ran up the spine
of this magnificent metropolis
as citizens began
fleeing for their lives!
[Bulma]
Oh.
Horrible...
Well, at least West City
hasn't been destroyed yet.
Most likely thanks
to Tien Shinhan
getting in Piccolo's way.
[static]
I wonder how well Tien is doing?
Uh...
If that dirt bag Piccolo
hurts him in any way,
I'll make him pay!
Oh, I have a feeling Piccolo
has his hands full.
That's right!
Yeah.
Mm...
A-A-A--
[BOTH gasp]
[LAUNCH]
A-Achoo!
--[BULMA screams]
--[YAMCHA] Uh!
[Yamcha]
Huh?
[gasping]
[screams]
So, are we going on a
picnic or something?
[BOTH sigh nervously]
[TIEN thinking] He defeated that
Drum creature with one blow...
One blow! I don't understand.
What happened to Goku? How could
he have become so powerful?
Of all people, I never
thought I would see you again.
How tenacious.
You dare get in my way?!
You bet I do. I will never stop
until I've defeated you!
You can try if you're feeling
suicidal... for you will die...
You think you're going
to be able to stop me?
Bigger and smarter adversaries
than you have tried and failed.
You'll see just how
much I've changed.
[PICCOLO] Heh. As tempting as
it is to disprove your boast,
I don't have the time...
There are people awaiting their
destruction in West City.
[growls]
Hm. This will have to be a quick
demonstration. I apologize.
Mmm.
[growling]
[GOKU]
Hm.
[PICCOLO screaming]
--[PICCOLO screaming]
--[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO]
Uh...
Impossible!
Yes! You blocked him!
[BOTH grunting]
[PICCOLO yelling]
--[GOKU grunting]
--[PICCOLO gasps]
[PICCOLO screams]
[gasps]
[screams]
What in this world is
making all of that noise?
[lock clicks]
Sire, it's King Piccolo!
I was afraid of that.
What's he destroying now?
Piccolo isn't destroying
anything, sir...
[KING]
Huh?!
He is fighting a young
child, and he is losing.
What?! He's losing?! Hurry!
[PIANO gasping]
What have you done to him?!
[PICCOLO grunting]
[growls]
I thought you said this
was going to be fast.
[PICCOLO] You insolent wretch!
Now you've really made me angry!
[PICCOLO, GOKU grunting]
[PICCOLO screams]
I don't believe my eyes!
He's actually dodging
Piccolo's attacks!
He is no ordinary child,
that's for sure!
[growling]
[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[PICCOLO growling]
[GOKU laughs]
[chuckles]
[PICCOLO growls]
No, Goku!
[PICCOLO gasps]
[yelps]
[PICCOLO panting]
You... filthy... human!
Astounding! Goku blocked every
blow Piccolo threw at him!
[PICCOLO] This isn't happening!
It can't be true!
[GOKU] I told you I wasn't the
same person you fought before!
[grunts] You think you can
attack me? Guess again, human!
You get one lucky
shot and suddenly
you think you're a big man!
I haven't begun to show
you my true power!
You've taken away
my close friends
and hurt innocent people!
[growls]
You'll pay for your crimes!
[GOKU growls]
[BOTH growling]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[PICCOLO thinking]
His eyes, so full of hatred.
He really thinks he can beat me!
Little does he know
how horrible I can be!
Huh?
[PICCOLO groaning]
[screams]
[whimpers]
[cheering]
That kid can punch!
Yes, sir!
[KING thinking] Get him,
boy! Do it for the world.
We're all depending on you!
[TIEN thinking]
Ah! He's not just stronger.
There's something more...
It's like watching a
different person. Watching--
Who am I kidding? He moved so
fast, I couldn't see him...
It was amazing. I can't
stop shaking!
[PICCOLO groaning]
[whimpering]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[growls]
Prepare... to die!
[GOKU yells]
[yelling]
[grunts]
Hmm.
Ah.
[PICCOLO yelping]
[grunts]
[PICCOLO gagging]
[groaning]
Incredible!
How can they move so fast?
Amazing!
[LAUNCH giggles]
Oh?
[giggles]
[chuckles]
[PICCOLO grunting]
--[GOKU grunting]
--[PICCOLO groaning]
[PICCOLO howls]
[panting]
[TIEN]
Great job, Goku! Don't let up!
[growling]
[gasps]
--[GOKU grunting]
--[PICCOLO groaning]
Perfect!
He did it!
We won!
[PICCOLO groaning]
Goku, what are you waiting for?!
[laughs]
[gasps]
[PICCOLO laughs]
It feels good, doesn't it?
We're no different, you and I.
We both love inflicting pain.
It's an intoxicating
feeling, isn't it?!
Don't listen to him, Goku.
He's just playing mind games.
Strike him down!
Stop talking and fight...
Where's all your power?
You said you'd finish me,
I'm still waiting!
He's bluffing! He knows
he can't beat you!
[PICCOLO]
My, aren't we sharp today?
Oh, you don't miss
a thing, do you?
You see, if I were to fight
you at full strength,
my life wouldn't last as long.
However, why save all the fun
for later when we
can party right now!
[screaming]
What-What's happening?!
[screaming continues]
I hope you're ready to die!
You should ask yourself
that question, Piccolo!
I didn't come here to lose!
You may have strength boy, but
bravado isn't your strong suit.
Stick to what you
do best and quit!
[GOKU]
I'm here to win!
[PICCOLO]
Not a chance!
[PICCOLO laughing]
Hold on, Goku! Fight him!
Give me all you've
got! I can take it!
No matter what you try,
I'm still gonna beat you!
Be careful what you ask
for. It may destroy you!
[grunting]
All you are is a bunch of talk!
[screaming]
See ya, kid!
[GOKU screaming]
Goku!
[whimpering]
Goku?!
[PICCOLO cackling]
It is over! Ha ha ha!
I am the winner!
Piccolo is invincible.
[PICCOLO] Poor deluded child.
He never stood a chance.
It's a shame your human
brains are so small.
Your ignorance almost takes
the fun out of killing you...
He has left a big hole to
fill. Care to join him?
What's the matter?
Has your nerve grown cold?!
Oh, You were so eager
to defeat me earlier!
You underestimate us all!
[GOKU]
Ka...
[gasps] Impossible!
[GOKU]
Me...
--[TIEN] Goku!
--[GOKU] Ha...
--No, he's dead!
[GOKU]
Me...
[laughs]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] King Piccolo's
astonishment is shared by all,
as Goku rises from his would-be
grave to gain the advantage.
Will Goku finally put an end
to King Piccolo's evil rampage?
Find out as the story continues,
next time on Dragon Ball!