[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
with the World
Martial Arts Tournament
only three years away,
it was obvious to Mr. Popo
that Goku still had
a lot of training to do
before he'd be ready.
[NARRATOR] Taking the young
warrior under his wing,
Mr. Popo put Goku
through his paces,
showing him
amazing new techniques
he had never seen before.
Turning a game of
hide and seek into
a high stakes struggle
between two warriors.
[NARRATOR] Desperately,
Goku tried everything he could
to escape his
persistent pursuer.
And for a moment it looked
like he just might do it.
Unfortunately,
he found out the hard way
that he still had
a lot to learn.
[GOKU]
You're too fast!
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, back on Earth,
Tien, Yamcha, Chaiotzu,
and Krillin found themselves
in some serious trouble.
The foursome had
stumbled across a village
that stood right in the
shadow of an active volcano!
It didn't take long for
the volcano to blow its top
and send red hot lava
gushing down the mountainside.
And with a village
right in its path,
there was no doubt
that if somebody
didn't do something fast,
it would be a hot time
in the old town tonight.
[TIEN] I'm going to try and
change the course of the lava.
But Tien, it's too--
I've got to try something
before it's too late.
It's the only chance we have.
We must save the village.
[NARRATOR]
Tien's a tough customer,
but even with
the help of his friends
can he prevent this
disaster from happening?
[VILLAGERS screaming]
Spirit! Please! Save us!
I beg of you! Please! Please!
[MINT] Elder!
You have to get out here!
[ELDER]
Oh, please!
[PAOL] Mint.
Leave him. We must go.
We can't just
leave the Elder here!
And what about
Krillin and his friends?
We've gotta
wait for them, don't we?
They're all crazy.
They think they can
stop the lava themselves?!
It won't work.
There is no way
that they can help us now.
[gasps]
No!
The mountain is angry, Mint.
Your friends are only
going to make things worse.
Can you really
stop the lava, Tien?
I don't know,
but no matter what happens,
now is the time to put
our training to the test.
[CHIAOTZU]
Mm.
Let's do it!
For the village!
Do you sense
my spiritual energy?
--I'm right here.
--Huh? Ah!
[POPO]
Now I'm here.
Don't follow my voice.
Try to sense my energy.
[POPO] If you focus
your mind, you will discover
that you don't always
need your eyes to see things
that are right in front of you.
That's easy for you to say!
I can't see
anything with this on!
Uuh... Uh-uh-ahh...
[groans]
It is only when you're
in touch with your own
spiritual energy that you will
be able to sense anyone elses.
Uh. My spirit?
Mhmmm.
[rumbling]
Stay alert, you guys.
[ALL gasping]
Uh! These earthquakes
aren't gonna make it easy
to reach the top.
[YAMCHA groans]
Just keep your
head down, Krillin.
[gasps]
It's not so bad up here.
[yells]
Ah!
Krillin!
[hollers]
Oh. Oooh!
[KRILLIN]
Thanks!
[groaning lightly]
Whew!
That was close! Thanks a lot!
Krillin, maybe the time
has come for you to
think about mastering
your flying technique?
--Uh-huh.
--[laughing]
[BOTH yell]
[MINT] Great Elder,
you cannot stay here!
It's too dangerous!
Come with us, we'll go some
place safe! Please, hurry!
I must stay here
until the very end.
I'll ask the mountain
spirit to forgive us
and spare the village.
It's all I can do now.
Oh great mountain spirit,
please forgive us!
Spare our village...
[MINT]
Elder, we really must leave!
Krillin come back!
I have to prove
something to myself.
Don't worry, I can handle this.
He's crazy!
[KRILLIN] I wish Mint were
here to see me do this.
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
Ha!
Hey! Look at that!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
Ow!
Nice try, but now it's my turn.
Get to the top of the mountain--
you can watch me from there.
Be careful, Tien.
Dodon Ray!
[grunts]
--[KRILLIN] Yay!
--[YAMCHA] Hm-hm!
[ALL yell]
[fast-paced
dramatic music plays]
Mmm! It didn't work!
Aah!
The village!
It'll be destroyed!
Mint's down there!
No, Krillin!
Great, he thinks he can
save the village by himself.
Then we'll let him think that.
[YAMCHA]
Hm? Hm!
But, look around!
[grunts]
We really could
use some rain. Ah!
There! That's it!
--Hm?
--What is it, Yamcha?
I think I can
cool things off a little.
Tien, try and
slow down the lava.
Good luck.
Ah! Nature against itself.
While he deals with the
water, I'll slow the fire.
Dodon Ray!
[KRILLIN] I've got to
protect the village
and Mint, no matter what.
[fast-paced
dramatic music plays]
[KRILLIN]
Where could she be?
Mint, you're okay!
Hey, Mint! Let's go!
It's not safe!
Let's get out of here!
The lava's coming!
Krillin, help us.
The Elder simply refuses
to abandon the village.
[ELDER] The great mountain
spirit will not desert us.
I know he will not let
the lava destroy our village.
But... it's coming
this way, sir.
You don't belong here.
Leave us alone.
We don't need help
from you or any outsider.
[grunts]
[KRILLIN, PAOL, and MINT gasp]
Dodon Ray! Aaah!
That did it.
Way to go, Tien! Yay!
[distant lava crackling,
rushing]
No...
[TIEN grunts]
--[MINT yells]
--[ELDER, KRILLIN, PAOL groan]
[yells, grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[KRILLIN grunting]
You're the greatest, Krillin.
[KRILLIN]
It was nothing!
[chuckles]
[distant rushing water]
Hmm...
[grunts]
Ka-me-ha-me...
Ha!
Ugh! Goku would deliver
a blast strong enough
to drown the whole forest.
I must keep trying!
Hmm!
What?!
You missed me!
[GOKU]
Uh.
[laughs]
[grunts]
Ka-me-ha-me...
Ha!
[laughing]
Would you look at
that. He did it!
[chuckles]
I'll say!
[ALL gasp]
[sizzling]
[VILLAGERS gasp, murmur]
[WOMAN] We're safe!
Our village is safe!
[ELDER]
I knew we would be saved.
My prayers were answered.
Ah yes. Once again
the mountain spirit
has spared our village from
certain disaster, my dear.
Mm! Ha-ha!
Well, it looks like we saved
the village, guys! Way to go!
[PAOL] Hah!
You didn't save anything!
The lava stopped because the
mountain spirit heard the Elder.
You and your friends ran
off and hid in the woods.
So don't try and take credit
for something you didn't do!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[PAOL] Now I think
it's time for all of you
to be on your way.
Thanks a lot.
[CHIAOTZU]
There's more trouble!
[KRILLIN]
Huh?
Where, Chaiotzu?
The mountain has not
finished erupting.
What?!
Aah!
[whimpers]
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[VILLAGERS screaming]
Please mountain spirit,
don't do this to us again!
Why are you so angry?
Let's get out of here right now!
Please, come with us!
[PAOL]
Mint!
Look out!
[screams]
[grunts]
[yells]
[ELDER whimpers]
You did it again, Krillin!
Ah! It's all in a days work!
It was a piece of rock--
I mean cake!
[chuckles]
Krillin. Thank you.
You saved us all.
Aah!
[ALL yell]
[VILLAGERS murmur, gasp]
Rats!
We can't stop this thing, Tien.
Let's go now.
While we still can.
No. I will not let
this mountain beat me.
I'm going to attack that lava
with every ounce
of strength in my body.
Okay, but you'll need help.
[KRILLIN grunts]
[grunts]
Dodon...!
Ka-me-ha-me...
Ray!
Ha!
[ALL gasp]
[TIEN]
Aah...
[YAMCHA]
Whoa!
[VILLAGERS clamor]
[gasps]
[VILLAGERS gasping, chatter]
We... We did it!
Yeah!
That fixed it
for good this time!
Even if the mountain
erupts again
the lava can't get
into the village anymore.
[MINT]
Krillin!
[giggles]
Here comes Mint.
[BOTH laughing]
[ALL]
Huh? [laugh]
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[NARRATOR] It seems to be
a happy ending. Or is it?
It's still three years until
the World Martial Arts
Tournament
and the competition
is going to be tough.
Goku is still trying his hardest
to learn some new
techniques from Mr. Popo,
but he's got a long way to go.
And once the tournament begins
there's going to be
no room for error.
To find out what's
going to happen next,
don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball.