[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Tambourine, brutal enforcer of
King Piccolo was sent to hunt
down and exterminate the members
of the Martial Arts Society.
[NARRATOR] One-by-one they fell.
No matter how confident...
[NARRATOR] ...or strong.
[NEWS] Police are baffled as
to the motives of the killer
and why only
martial artists are targeted.
[NARRATOR]
Alerted to the danger,
Master Roshi and his team fled
Kame Island in search of safety.
[NARRATOR] King Piccolo
hatched a new warrior, Cymbal,
and sent him on a mission
to retrieve the
remaining six Dragon Balls.
Who do you serve my child?
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Goku,
ravaged from his confrontation
with Tambourine,
stumbled through the jungle,
where he faced an even
greater adversary--hunger!
I can't go on.
Gotta eat something.
[NARRATOR] Luckily,
Goku found some ammunition.
[NARRATOR] Things were
looking up for our young hero,
until he was suddenly
hit with another surprise.
[GOKU]
I know you're there!
Come out and face me you coward!
I'm not a coward.
You're the sneak
that stole my food!
[NARRATOR]
Expecting to find Tambourine,
Goku was surprised
by the new face.
But is the stranger friendly,
or another adversary
for Goku to fight?
[YAJIROBE] Hmm...
Ya thief!
Huh? What's that?
You heard!
I'm not a thief! I didn't
steal anything of yours!
Oh yeah?!
Well, I don't recall inviting
you to eat my brektis!
[GOKU] What's brektis?
It sounds awful.
My fish!
Look, I don't steal.
Can you prove
it's your brektis fish?
Hey, wait a minute.
Are you calling me a liar?!
If so, you'd better
be prepared to fight.
[GOKU] Okay.
I don't know where
you're from, big hair.
But around here, it's not polite
to steal other people's food!
Oh, I see.
But you're fine with throwing
giant boulders at strangers,
is that it?
My Dragon Ball! Now I get it.
You tried to hurt me because
you're helping that monster,
weren't you?
Monster?
You know who I'm talking about.
The monster. He's big and
green and he's got giant wings!
He took my
friend Krillin's life.
And so now I'm after his!
Hey, that's a nice story,
but my belly is still empty.
You stole food, now pay for it.
[YAJIROBE]
You're nothing but a thief!
Liar!
I'd rather be a liar
than a thief! Thief!
So you admit that you're lying!
Why you!
[growls] Take that back!
Uh-uh!
[grunts]
You used your head.
That wasn't fair!
[chuckles]
I got you!
[YAJIROBE]
You hurt my nose!
Here, have a foot!
Hyaah!
My foot's stronger.
Oh well, have a nice nap.
Ready to give up?
If so, I'll help you out.
[gasps]
[GOKU thinking] I don't get it.
I kicked him as hard as I could.
Who is this guy?
[YAJIROBE thinking] I've never
been hit so hard in my life.
What's he made of, solid stone?!
[YAJIROBE thinking]
This isn't going to be
as easy as I thought.
[GOKU thinking] I still don't
know what brektis is.
[humming]
That one's all done.
Hardly worth the
effort, but finished.
Hmmm... Who's my next victim?
[ROSHI]
You kids don't worry.
You should be safe
here on this island.
But that doesn't mean you
don't stay on your guard.
[BULMA] Yeah, well,
that's really great advice
Master Roshi,
but we can't hide forever.
If we don't find the Dragon
Balls before King Piccolo,
none of us will be safe.
Hmmm...
You be careful, okay.
[CHIAOTZU]
We will.
[YAMCHA]
No, it isn't fair!
[CHIAOTZU]
Huh?
My darn leg.
If it wasn't all busted up,
I could go with you guys.
Don't worry. Just stay here
and get some rest.
It's better this way.
If anything happens to us,
you'll be the only one left.
[gasps]
Promise me, please come back!
Mhmm.
[LAUNCH]
That's enough of that!
Don't talk like
you're not coming home!
If any of you get splattered,
I swear I'll fill you
with so many bullets,
you'll jump back to life
just to beg me for mercy!
Uh, right.
Huh?
Oh, I sure hope we
see those guys again.
Could you be any
more pessimistic?!
Show a little faith.
They're going to be just fine!
At least, I hope so.
Enough about that.
Come on. I'll make a freezing
capsule to preserve Krillin.
Eh heh heh heh heh.
We've spent a lot
of time together,
but we know so
little of each other.
So, I brought you
my family album.
Thought you might want
to look at some pictures.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Emperor please.
No one wants to see that.
[PILAF] I've got double prints
if you see some you like.
Huh?
[SHU]
Uh, sire...
He doesn't share
your enthusiasm.
[PIANO] You silly worm.
His majesty is sleeping.
Huh?
He can rest with
both his eyes open,
especially when he's bored.
Whew...
Finished.
Ooh! What a beautiful chamber.
Thank you. Now let's
place Krillin inside, gently.
Hmph. He looks happy.
Probably loves the attention.
[chuckles]
He sure seems
comfortable in there.
Alright, that's it.
Time to close 'em up.
Whoa, tiny.
Don't mix 'em up
with your vitamins. Heh.
Hmmm... Where's a
good place to keep him?
[BULMA]
This should do the trick.
[OOLONG]
Right.
I'm sure Krillin loves being
stuffed next to your socks.
And your bloomers.
[BULMA]
I heard that!
Wait, just kidding!
I should be close.
[laughs]
All right, I can tell
you're not from around here.
What do ya call
yourself, big hair?
My name is Goku.
What do I call you?
I'm Yajirobe.
Yajirobe. That's funny.
Nyaaaah!
It beats Goku.
[GOKU growls]
That does it!
Huh?
Uh?
What's wrong with you?
Uh...
Hey, that Dragon Ball
you're wearing, it's not mine.
You have the one-star ball,
not the four!
I don't understand.
Where in the world
did you find yours?!
I found it in the jungle
somewhere about three years ago.
Wait, three years.
Then... Hmm...
Boy, do I feel silly.
This is all just
a misunderstanding.
There's no way you could
have helped that monster!
I told you I wasn't a liar.
But you did steal... my fish!
[giggles]
Do you have any
idea how long it takes
to cook a fish that size?
It takes hours!
[GOKU]
Look, that's him.
[YAJIROBE]
What an ugly bird.
You won't get away this time!
[CYMBAL chuckles]
How long you live depends
on your answer to my question.
It looks like him, but that's
not the monster I fought.
[YAJIROBE]
All right, be quick.
What do you want from us?
I seek a little orange
ball with stars on it.
If either of you have seen one,
you'd better tell me or
suffer the consequences.
If you want someone's help,
you should learn to ask nicely.
Hmmm?
[laughs] I don't believe it!
Score!
Nice necklace.
Give it here!
Uh, if you're interested in the
Dragon Balls, that means that
you must be partners
with the same monster
who destroyed my friend Krillin
and that makes you my enemy!
Huh? You'd better talk some
sense into you friend.
Choose your words
carefully, Monster.
He's not my friend.
Monster, do you have a
friend with a mouth like this?
And eyes like this?
And he's got big wings,
and he's mean and ugly,
but he's not as big as you?
[CYMBAL] Hmmm...
That sounds like, Tambourine.
Then he's the one I'm after.
I couldn't care less.
I'm here for the
Dragon Ball. Period!
Sorry, I like it.
If you want one,
go find your own.
This one belongs to me.
So what?
I like yours just fine, boy.
Heh heh heh.
Since you're so cocky,
I'd be happy to crush every
bone in your body to get it!
Hmph! Try it.
I'll break you in half.
No way. I'll take
care of this creature.
[YAJIROBE]
Stay back. He's mine.
I'm fighting him.
His ally killed my best friend.
I don't care.
Your problems don't concern me.
This green thing insulted me
and now he's going to pay.
Why are you so stubborn?
He's my new brektis.
Huh?!
There's an easy way
to settle this.
Fine!
--I choose rock.
--I choose paper!
--I choose rock!
You can't be serious.
You're playing over
who will fight me?
--I choose scissors!
Oh come on,
that's not how you play.
Everyone knows that
dynamite always wins!
--Choose rock. I choose paper!
--Choose rock! I choose paper!
[CYMBAL grumbles]
--[YAJIROBE] I choose paper!
--[GOKU] I choose rock!
Hah! I win! Paper can
wrap around the rock, silly!
[growls] I know, I know!
[CYMBAL growls]
Try and do your worst. I want
this fight to last a while.
Heh heh heh!
If you're so eager to die,
who am I to stand in your way?!
I'll be eating you soon!
Hah hah hah! You were saying?
It looks like the only thing
that you'll be eating is dirt!
[YAJIROBE]
Hmmm...
Huh?
It's been a strange day.
I keep meeting strong enemies.
Ha! It's not the enemies'
strength. You're just weak.
[GOKU laughs]
There is no weakness
in me, monster!
Big words for small prey!
Hey, you don't look
as scary with less teeth.
You're just as ugly, though.
You'll pay for that!
[chuckles] Let's see
how much you like dancing!
[YAJIROBE]
Hmmm?
[gasps]
[laughs]
That lightning's a neat trick.
No one told me we
were using weapons!
Sure you don't want help?
Positive! I can handle
this beast by myself!
All right! Let's finish this!
Hahaha!
You're a good dancer.
Dance! Dance!
Be silent! And fight...
...with honor to the end!
Aaaattack!
Hahaha! That's it!
Come meet your destruction!
[GOKU]
Hmmm?
Wow! You're fast!
[PICCOLO gasps]
Piccolo, what's wrong?
You look ill.
Cymbal has failed me.
[NARRATOR] Clearly Yajirobe
is no ordinary being.
But who is he?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!