[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
I'm coming! Hang on, Grandpa!
Not good...
It's a fake!
It's just a glass bead!
It's here, soewhere, buried
under all this old crap.
Time's up, old man.
[gunshots]
[NARRATOR] As the search
below erupts into chaos,
the real Dragon Ball
has taken wing
and now soars silently
in the distance.
Goku has also taken to the skies
unaware that the Dragon Ball
he chases is actually a fake
and unaware that a
dangerous new enemy
is also on the hunt.
[KUMA] Sir, the Dragon Ball
in Colonel Silver's sector
has begun moving
to the northwest.
[RED] Let him
know immediately.
[RED chuckles]
It's all falling into place.
My men have located each
of the seven balls.
It's only a matter of time
before they retrieve them
and I rule the world!
[SILVER] Foolish peasant!
[beeping]
[SILVER] Colonel Silver here.
[KUMA] Silver, listen up!
[KUMA] The Dragon Ball
is moving north-northwest.
Begin pursuit at once.
I understand.
[SILVER]
Soldiers, we're clearing out!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[GOKU] I don't get it.
They have Grandpa's
Dragon Ball in there,
but the radar still says I'm
getting farther away from it.
I guess it's broken,
but oh well...
I don't need it anymore!
I know where to go!
[PILAF sobbing]
Oh, Sire, you paid a
fortune for this useless thing.
Idiot!
You don't need to
remind me of that!
Um, Sire,
according to the radar...
the Dragon Ball is
moving away from this ship.
Then follow it, fool!
What in the...?
That's it!
You, get lost!
Sire!
Help me!!
I'll help if yo promise to
give me back my grandpa.
Your grandpa?
What about your grandpa?
Who knows your grandpa??!!
I mean my
grandpa's Dragon Ball!
Give it back!
That cheap glass marble?
That was an imitation!
W-Wait! I give up!
It's all yours! You can have it!
So help meeeeee!
[bonk]
Hey you...
Hey, snap out of it.
You made a promise.
[SHU] Oh, it looks awful.
The boss'll be furious.
[MAI] I hope we
found all the pieces.
How much longer?
Oh, well, I'm sure they'll
find it any minute.
It's around here somewhere,
but you know how it is
tryng to say organized.
While you're waiting,
how about a nice cup of tea?
Here it is!
[SHU] As good as new!
Yeow!
Ah! I see it's restored!
Uh, I mean, you found
where it was stored...
Hey, it's my grandpa!
Oh, no!
You have to hold
these things carefully.
Grab it lightly!
Lightly?
Oh, yea, very lightly.
[GOKU] I really missed it!
Oh... It's cracked!
[PILAF] OK!
Thanks for stopping by...
Here's your little ball...
Don't be a stranger, now.
Now listen you two!
Time to get back to business.
Find that real one!
Yessir!
What was that about?!
No! My Dragon Ball!
Grandpa!!
Got it. Got it. Got it.
Uh... How did that happen?
[NARRATOR]
Not far away, in the land
where Fire Mountain once stood,
the Ox King has
given up his evil ways
has made peace
with the villagers.
He and his daughter, Chichi,
are honored by the people now,
and enjoy life in
this tranquil town.
[CHICHI] Oh, where have
you gone, my darling Goku?
[CHICHI] I hope he
hasn't forgotten me
after all this time.
I'll just die if
I don't see him soon!
[OX KING] Chichi!
[CHICHI] Hmm? Oh! Hi, Dad.
You're just crazy about
that boy, Goku, aren't you?
Well, he's kind of... sweet.
[OX KING]
You know, the old housekeeper
fancies herself
a bit of a psychic.
Maybe she can help you find him.
Oh! Would she do that?
[chanting]
Spirit of Fire Mountain,
all powerful.
Will you help
this lovesick fool?
She can't find her love today.
Will you please
point out the way?
Ohhh!
Tell me! What is it?
[HOUSEKEEPER]
He's approaching...
Well, when will he be here?
[HOUSEKEEPER] Very soon...
Did'ya hear that Chichi?
Your Goku is heading
to our village!
Oh, boy!
Goku will fall in love with me
and we'll be married and
we'll live happily ever after!
Married!
Aren't you too young
to be getting married?
Besides, how well
do you know this boy?
Oh, Daddy.
When it's the right time,
you just know it.
Well, then, I've got
a lot of planning to do!
[CHICHI] Planning? What for?
Well, only the
very finest wedding
will do for the daughter
of the great Ox King.
I have to get ready!
Oh... my... is this real?
Ah hahaha! I'm getting married!
[HOUSEKEEPER thinking]
Uh-oh, what just happened here?
Good news! Everyone!
Good news!
There's gonna be a wedding!
[KUMA] The Dragon Ball
is baring towards
point B3 moving north-northwest
at a rate of 50 miles an hour.
So far, we still have
no visual confirmation.
We'll stay on alert though, sir.
Look here, Colonel.
I think we've found it.
It seems to be
ahead to our left.
Jackpot, we have a visual.
[SILVER] Wh-What? What the...
This will make an
excellent wedding feast.
Chichi will be so happy!
[SOLDIER A] Colonel,
that's the Ox King!
[SILVER] I see that...
our job just got
considerably harder.
Heads up!
An unknown aircraft
in the vicinity.
Soldier, fly us to cover.
Sire, I'm afraid
we've run into trouble.
I think that's the Ox King.
I've heard he
is really ruthless.
Nonsense!
My rise to power will
not be stopped by some...
some... cow-man!
Now you find a way
to get down there
and bring me that ball
or you'll both be crying
for your mommies
But Sire, he's a monster.
Yesh, he's really scary,
and fearless and
strong and evil.
All the villagers
are petrified of him.
They used to call him the...
the... Devil King!
Uh... Devil King you say?
Is this the first
you've ever heard of him?
Uh, well, of course it isn't...
b-but you know how
these stories can be inflated.
Welcome, Sir.
May I say it is an honor
to help prepare your
daughter's wedding.
I'm sure she'll be very happy.
The entire village is
buzzing about the big party,
and especially the feast!
[OX KING] Thank you very much.
I'll give the little bride
your blessings.
Huh?
Sir, what's that over there?
[OX KING] Where?
Oh! Is it the guest of honor?
Ready! Man your
positions for attack mode.
[MAI] Wait a minute, Emperor.
Oh, what now, Mai?
[MAI] Take a look at this, Sire.
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[PILAF] Welcome back
Gokowa? Huh?
[SHU] I think that's Goku, Sire.
[PILAF] Don't correct me!
[SHU thinking]
Oh, me and my big mouth!
[MAI] Wait. Isn't Goku
that kid with the cloud?
I don't get it.
Why does Goku get this
big welcoming when I,
the great Emperor, get zilch?
They must be expecting Goku.
[OX KING] Chichi! Chichi!
Where did you run off to?
Chichi!
Did you see
which way that girl went?
[HOUSEKEEPER]
Um... I think she went out
to pick some flowers
for her bouquet.
My little girl's
picking her bouquet?
I don't believe it.
Oh, the children
just grow up so fast.
Emperor, the disguise is ready.
Oh, Shu-uuu!
Your costume awaits you.
[PILAF] Ah-ha! They'll
never be able to tell.
[SHU] But what if
they find me out?
I'm a terrible actor.
You quit that snivelling!
You see, it is more logical
to get the Dragon Ball
the sneaky way than
to have to battle this
big ox on his home field!
[SHU] But I'm even
bad at charades!
And keep your mouth shut!
You sound nothing like Goku!
[SHU] Whatever you say.
If you weren't
the one with the tail,
I sure wouldn't trust you
with anything this important.
Don't blow it!
[SHU] Yes sir.
Ha-ha! Here's the groom-to-be.
[VILLAGERS cheering]
Welcome to my village,
young man.
Chichi's out, but don't worry,
the wedding's all planned.
It's the finest wedding
in the land, right?
[cheering]
[SHU] W-Wedding?
Hey, you're not getting
cold feet are you, son?
And who might you two be?
Uh... ah... uh...
We're his cousins!
I gotta find something to eat.
[stomach growls]
I'm just starving.
Huh?
[munching sounds]
[girl humming]
Hey, Chichi!
It's me, Goku!
Goku, I can't believe you
came all this way for me!
What are you talking about?
I was just picking flowers
for the wedding, see?
Oh... I didn't think
this day would ever
come, did you?
Well, yeah.
Tomorrow always comes.
Oh, Goku, you big joker!
Ouch! You made me
hurt my head and my tail!
Oh, I've got to
be more lady-like.
That's okay...
You want an apple?
Oh! For me?
[GOKU] Sure, I have plenty.
[SHU]
Emperor, I can't get married!
I don't even know her!
Moron, nobody said
you have to marry her.
[SHU] But this is
Goku's wedding, isn't it?
[PILAF] You just keep
pretending until
we get the Dragon Ball,
then we'll scram!
[SHU] Yes, Sire.
Goku, I'm sorry for the waiting.
She should be here by now.
[SHU] Oh, it's no hurry.
You idiot!
Can't you think on your own!
Tell him you're hungry
so we can find the ball
and sneak out before
she gets back!
[SHU] Oh... Okay!
Wow, I sure am starving
[sighs]
Oh, of course, forgive
me for my rudeness.
Why don't we eat now
and have the big celebration
whenever she gets back?
Hey! Bring out the food!
Oh, wow. There it is.
Yes, Mai. I can almost taste it.
Lts have a toast
to the happy couple...
even though the bride
is still missing...
May all your days
be very bright,
and your battles short!
Cheers!
[cheering]
Goku, you are our special guest.
If there's anything you need,
you just let me know.
Okay everybody, let's eat!
Hey, tell him you
want the big one.
[SHU] But I'm not really hungry.
Just do what I say!
Now what are you
two whispering about?
Let me in on the secret.
Oh, well,
Goku's just embarrassed,
but he told me he
is really hungry
and doesn't think this little
bird is enough to fill him up.
Of course!
The groom needs his strength!
Don't be so shy...
we're practically
family already.
Fathers and sons should
tell each other everything.
How can I help if you won't
tell me what you want, son?
Look a flying pig!
Hold on, pigs don't fly.
What is this?
Who in the world would want
to ruin my sweet
little girl's wedding day?
I'll get the scoundrel
who did this!
Let's move it!
I'm afraid it's now or never!
Don't be foolish!
This is the best chance to
get the ball that we've had yet!
Shu, come on now,
you've got to pull
yourself together, man!
[SHU] Oh yes sir,
I'm very hungry.
He's such a Neanderthal!
Colonel, do we retreat?
No, hold your ground.
I'll take care of him.
Oh, I can't see!
The net!
Never tangle with
the Red Ribbon Army!
All available men!
Get down there
and find that ball!
At last... it's all mine!
Huh?
[BOTH] Come on,
come on, come on, come on...
Get him!
So I was thinking,
when we get married I want to
have a really big family, okay?
Do you feel the same?
[GOKU]
Huh? I think I fell asleep.
Oh, you're so goofy!
Why are you teasing me?
Ouch!
Why do you keep hitting me?
Oh... what's that?
Oh! That's coming
from my village!
Uh... uh-oh!
Come to me Flying Nimbus!
Hey, come on,
let's check it out.
[CHICHI] Okay.
[NARRATOR] Will the Red Ribbon
Army allow Emperor Pilaf
to escape with the Dragon Ball?
Will Goku and Chichi
get to the village
in time to help
the great Ox King?
Is the wedding still on?
Tune in to our next
adventure to find out!