[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball,
the morning came ridiculously
early for Goku and Krillin
who hope to enter the upcoming
World Martial Arts Tournament...
Even before the
rooster's first call,
the boys had begun their
intensive physical training
under Master Roshi's
expert gaze.
[NARRATOR] Their first task--
Deliver the 4:30 AM shipment
of milk around the island!
Normally this is
done by helicopter,
but as the boys soon learned,
convenience is not the
M.O. of Turtle Hermit Training!
They zigzagged through
orchards to test agility...
They struggled up mountain
steps to test endurance--
which Krillin
didn't have much of--
and they teetered over dangerous
canyons to test their balance.
[NARRATOR] The training was
hard and will only get harder,
but as any warrior knows,
it's important to keep moving.
[NARRATOR] Especially when
there's a T-Rex on your heels!
[DOJO MASTER]
You live--fighting...!
You breathe--fighting...!
You eat--fighting!
[DOJO MASTER] Drink...
Fight...! Sleep...! Fight!
[NARRATOR] Across the land,
fighters train themselves
for the upcoming World
Martial Arts Tournament.
[AX MAN roars]
[growls]
Raaargh!
[NARRATOR] In but
a few short months,
the world's fiercest warriors
will gather together--
all sharing a single desire...
That tournament
belt will be mine!!!
[chuckles]
Two hundred...
and twelve...! Thirteen!!
Fourteen...!
Two hundred fifteen...! Sixteen!
Lie down now
and you'll be kicked
out of the tournament
in the preliminary round!
Now get yourself up!!
[panting]
I just barely made it...
I'm glad we're done...
What's that you say?
He's glad we're done...
With today's training, I mean...
Oh please...!
That run was only
early morning exercise!!
Uh?
Eh?
[groaning]
Now it's time for
mid-morning exercises!
[gasps]
You're gonna try your
hands at agriculture!
[ROSHI] For that man over there!
Agri--what?
[ROSHI] Excuse me, sir!
[KRILLIN] Agriculture...
It's a big word that means
"playing with dirt"...
[GOKU] Oh...
[FARMER] Of course Master Roshi!
Sure, that's fine.
Thanks. They'll be so happy...
Come on boys...!
Time to get dirty!!
First we're the milk men and
now we're stinkin' farmers...
We never did this
at Orin Temple!
Think I'll just supervise...
Hold on there...!
Don't use the tool!
[GOKU and KRILLIN]
Huh?
This exercise is
for the strength
and dexterity
of your hands,
so of course it won't work
unless it's done bare-handed!
Like with our fingers?!!
You betcha.
[ROSHI] Beautiful day, isn't it?
[FARMER] Yes, it is!
Oh...! My fingernails are gone!
So, ready to quit, Krillin?
Huh? No.
I gotta say...
Those boys work like tractors!
[GOKU] Master Roshi...
[KRILLIN]
Stop with the tingling!
We finished it...
That's excellent work boys...!
But you must learn
to move faster...
The amount of land you
till will increase every day.
Now, who wants breakfast?
Ooh... Hunger...
Give me a chicken
and I'll eat it raw...
[LAUNCH] Perfect!
Well it's about time...!
Hurry up so it doesn't
get cold, you guys!
[ROSHI] Wait for Roshi!!!
[LAUNCH] Let's say
our grace first
then we'll eat
all this food, okay?
[LAUNCH and KRILLIN and ROSHI]
Thanks very much!
Wait...! Not the pepper...!
She's a land mine!
[KRILLIN] What?!
Who is?? I-- Uh-oh...
[sneezes]
[sinister laughter]
Alright...
Dessert... is... on... me!
You cowards!
Let's go out to eat!
More rice please!
Me too!
Each day we'll be
hitting the books
from now until lunchtime...
A strong body is pointless
unless you know how to use it...
And that takes brain-power!
Oh... But I don't have that!
So the wonder-boy
has a weakness...
First off... literature...!
Goku, please read
from page fourteen.
[GOKU groans] "Ooh...
Susie that tickles...
What if they find us here?"
...said Bill.
But Susie did not stop,
holding his foot
lightly in her hand...
[KRILLIN] And that means,
X would equal...
Well, wait...
How do you spell X...?
Maybe it's time we had lunch...
[GOKU cheers]
How silly...!
I forgot the soup!
Lunch isn't
right without it!
Yes... We'll spend this
hour on good old napping!
Work hard, study well,
and eat and sleep plenty...!
That's the Turtle Hermit
way to learn!
Hey... Master...
What's up?
Are there gonna be a lot
of really strong fighters
at this tournament we're in?
Oh, you bet...!
This tournament
is like a big magnet
for all the greatest
fighters across the globe!
I can't wait...
Some people spend
their whole lives
training just to make it
through the qualifying round!
So... what if while we're
lying in our hammocks,
someone else out
there is training
and getting stronger than us?
How do we know?
[ROSHI] The truth, Goku,
is that we can't know...
But I think you'll
find that everyone,
even the strongest warriors,
need their shuteye...
And this will be your
mid-afternoon training...
Construction work helps
with balance and muscle-size,
and could earn you boys some
extra dollars on the side!
[FOREMAN] You sure
these kiddos can work?
They look a little
small for a pickax!
Oh, just wait...!
Once you see these two work
you'll want to pay them
five times the typical salary!
[FOREMAN] Five times...?!
You must think I'm a fool!!
Well let's wait
until you see them
before we decide that...
Start diggin' boys!
Do... we... still have
to use bare hands?
Hmm... Not this time, Krillin.
Just no power-tools, okay?
Work force keeps
gettin' younger...
What... are they??
Turn up the motor boys
or you'll never make
it to the tournament!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Stay with it, old buddy...!
Stay with it until
you can beat them!
Okay, you win...
You are such a
miserable runt...!
I can't believe the Master
wastes his time on you!
Come on, little Krillin!
Don't you want to fight?
Oh look...!
He almost dodged it!
Don't worry...!
There's always the circus!
So that's why the
Master kept him...!
He makes such an
excellent punching bag!
[laughter]
All right! All right!
I'll pay whatever wage
you want for them!!!
After the sweat
you boys worked up
at that last site I'm having
you jump in the lake!
You mean there's more!
Of course!
Isn't the sun still up?
Master...!
When are you gonna start
teaching us fighting moves?
Now don't get jumpy...!
There are certain
basics you need
before learning Martial Arts
and you boys aren't there yet!
I will be delighted
to teach you the secrets
of Martial Arts just as
soon as you're strong enough
to move this rock!
What...? Move that thing...?
Well I don't mean
any disrespect Master,
but that's impossible!!
Oh really?
Impossible, is it...?
Well if you two stop complaining
and stick with my program...
One day you'll
be able to do this too!
[KRILLIN] Yes, master!
[GOKU grunting]
Now why do
I get the feeling
that you missed the entire
point of my lecture, Goku?
Hey look...!
You can teach us now!
Krillin wants
everybody to know
that he's
speechless right now...
[chuckles] Oh yeah...?
Well that's my mistake...!
Guess I was in such a hurry
that I pushed the wrong rock...!
I mean anyone and
his great-grandmother
could push a rock of that size!
[ROSHI] There!
That's the rock I meant...!
Once you move that then you're
ready for Martial Arts...!
Yup!
Whoa...! That one's giant!!
Master Roshi,
it just won't move!
Naturally, son...!
That all comes with
dedicated training!
[GOKU] Can you move it then?
[ROSHI] Of course!
Really...?! Come on
Master let us see!
[ROSHI] What do you say
we go do some training...?
The clock is
ticking you know...!
[ROSHI] Now I want you
to swim ten laps, okay...?
And try not to splash
each other in the eyes!
Well that's quite a relief...
Some easy stuff at last!
Ready! Set! Swim!
I guess Master Roshi is
rewarding us for good behavior.
Yeah it's kinda
like taking a bath!
You better watch out boys,
there're some big fish in there!
[KRILLIN] What kind of big fish?
[ROSHI] Sharks, mostly...!
[GOKU] Did you feel that?
[KRILLIN] Feel what?
That's not a lap Krillin...!
You forgot to touch the
other side of the shore!
Are you kidding me?
At least we're safe...
Hey...! You haven't
finished swimming!
Now that's what
I call motivation!
[ROSHI] Good job, boys!
Are you ready
for the next lesson?
This exercise will
test your reflexes
and dodging speed!
Why'd you tie us up
with rope Master Roshi?
Sometimes when
fighting we get cornered
and must dodge the enemy
in a limited space...!
You see?
[ROSHI] Good luck men!
Hold on... What
are we dodging from?
Concentrate hard and
you won't get stung!
Don't just run!
Dodge! Dodge!
[ROSHI] Concentrate boys!
Obviously we'll have to
work on your dodging ability...
But on the bright side,
you've completed your
first full day of training!
Master...
Please say our
training isn't going to be
this difficult
every single day...
Of course not Krillin.
It will be much more difficult!
For the next
few months you'll be
doing the exact same
training schedule as today...
But you'll be wearing these
stylish fifty-pound
turtle shells!
[NARRATOR] Guess that's why they
call him the Turtle Hermit...!
[NARRATOR] Goku and Krillin
have their hands full,
but it should all pay off ...!
Because the World Martial Arts
Tournament is coming soon!