[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
King Piccolo's sinister plot
to regain his youth
through the power of the
Dragon Balls was revealed.
The only obstacle in his
way was Master Roshi,
determined to prevent the
monster from claiming his prize
and taking over the world.
Piccolo proved to be
a dangerous adversary.
Attempting to
capture the creature,
the Turtle Hermit
went on the offensive
using the
Evil Containment Wave
to trap Piccolo
in the Electronic Jar.
He failed.
I-I missed it!
[NARRATOR] By a twist of fate,
the battle shifted
in favor of Piccolo,
who, while exhausted from
the ordeal, retained control.
Master Roshi had
depleted all his energy,
and with nothing left to give,
succumbed to fatigue.
King Piccolo
claimed the Dragon Balls
and called forth
the Eternal Dragon.
Magnificent!
[screaming]
Incredible!
[LAUNCH]
What's going on?!
There wasn't supposed
to be a storm today!
Why do we even have weathermen?!
[OOLONG]
It can't be a solar eclipse.
We'd need a moon for that!
All seven Dragon Balls
are now gathered together.
Someone must have called
upon the Eternal Dragon.
Hmm. It could be Master Roshi
or King Piccolo!
I wonder which one!
I don't want to know!
[DRAGON roaring]
The Eternal Dragon! You're here!
After all this time, my greatest
desire will finally come true!
[laughing]
[TIEN thinking]
Chiaotzu! Can you hear me?
Tien Shinhan!
[TIEN thinking] We have to
do something about this!
Now I want you to
listen to me very carefully.
I'm losing consciousness
because of that strange medicine
Master Roshi gave me.
This is up to you.
Before Piccolo
can make his wish,
I want you to make your own.
Tell the Dragon you wish that
King Piccolo would disappear
from this world forever!
Mm-hmm! Okay!
I will grant one wish.
Tell me what it is you desire.
At last!
I...
I wish for...
Make King Piccolo...
...disappear...
...from this...
[CHIAOTZU yelling]
Tien...
Chiaotzu!
[TIEN thinking]
No! Please no, not him!
I despise uninvited guests.
What do you wish for?
I wish to be made young again!
Restore my youth and power.
Return to me what time
has stolen! Can you do this?!
As you wish.
It's happening!
His Majesty is growing young!
[laughing]
It worked!
I'm young again! I am...
...born anew!
[PILAF] We won! We won!
His youth has returned!
Hooray for King Piccolo!
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Your wish has been granted.
I take my leave.
There's one more thing
you can do for me.
[roaring]
They are nothing but stones now.
[laughing]
And the Dragon is dead!
My enemies are vanquished.
No one will ever
challenge me again!
It is perfect!
I have been reborn!
Congratulations, sire.
You did it!
I'm looking forward to the day
King Piccolo conquers the world.
Then he'll...
...be so grateful, he'll give
you that swampland you wanted!
[CROWD] Pilaf! Pilaf!
[chanting continues]
Hi!
[giggling]
I feel invincible!
Hey! Look at that! It's gotten
bright all of a sudden!
I can't get a signal
on the Dragon Balls.
I was right. Someone
already called the Dragon.
I'd sure like to see
this dragon of yours.
I hope it wasn't Piccolo.
There's no telling
what he'd ask for.
Whoa! I think I see it!
Is that Korin's Tower up ahead?
[BULMA]
It just went dead!
The signal is gone!
All right. So what
explanations are we looking at?
The most positive scenario is
that Master Roshi was able
to call for the Eternal Dragon
before King Piccolo.
If that's the case, the monsters
are no longer on this world.
Oh yeah, good one.
It sounds reasonable enough.
I mean, justice always
prevails in the end, right?
I sure hope
that's what happened.
If Master Roshi didn't win,
and King Piccolo
used the Dragon Balls,
then I wonder what
it is he wished for.
From what we know of him,
I'd say he wished
for something diabolical,
like the end of the world.
[shrieks]
Mm-hmm! That's quite possible.
Gee, why is everyone so
pessimistic around here?
[laughs awkwardly]
Anyway, we can't afford
to hang around here.
Bulma, give me the last
coordinates on the radar
before it died.
I'll go check it out.
Wait a minute, Yamcha. I think
you're jumping the gun here.
If you're right and
Master Roshi did win,
then he'll probably
try to reach us here.
I think we should just
stay put and ride it out.
I know, you're probably right.
I'm just tired of doing nothing!
I'm starving.
Please tell me this tower we're
heading for has some good food!
I can guarantee it.
By the way, you still haven't
told me about the person
you're going to meet
if we get there.
His name is Korin.
He's a master of martial arts.
I used to take lessons
from him a long time ago.
He really knows his stuff, huh?
Who do you think is stronger?
Korin or King Piccolo?
Hmm. It's hard to say.
You have to think about it?
Man, this cat must be strong!
So what does
he look like, anyway?
Hmm... He's furry
and has big ears.
Huh?!
In other words,
he's an ugly beast.
This is a friend of yours?
He doesn't sound nice to me.
He's not going to try and
eat us for brektis, is he?
[laughs]
You're funny, Yajirobe.
It's time to
get down to business.
This world will soon be mine!
Yes! The world will soon
be under our control!
Full speed ahead!
Take me to the king's castle!
I'm don't think
the direct approach
is the way to handle this.
Hm? Do my tactics trouble you?
Of course not!
You have great tactics!
It's that this
castle we're going to
has some impressive weapons
and I thought maybe
we should get an... upgrade?
No, wait! Scratch that!
We don't need an upgrade.
Our current systems
should do just fine!
[laughing tauntingly]
You foolish twerp! Now that King
Piccolo has regained his youth,
no weapon on the
planet can destroy him.
Yes, I see!
Well, uh, no sense in
hanging around here any longer.
We've got a castle to conquer!
[VILLAGER] Sire, I beg of you.
Please help my village.
This drought has
lasted over 6 months!
There isn't enough
water for drinking,
let alone to grow our crops.
We can't last much longer.
I understand your needs.
I will help.
Sire, you mean--
I will send the Aqua-Squad
to your aid immediately.
Thank you, sire!
Do not thank me.
I share your happiness.
My lifelong dream is that
everyone in the world
will one day live
in perfect harmony.
Sire.
[TIEN thinking]
Master Roshi! Chiaotzu!
I can't believe you're gone.
I never should have sent
you out there, Chiaotzu.
Master told us to stay
out of it, but I didn't listen.
Piccolo! I'll never
forgive you for this!
I know I can't defeat Piccolo,
but I have to avenge
my friends. I have to!
I-I can't believe it.
Impossible!
Evil Containment!
[screaming]
The wave...
If only I could use it!
We'll be arriving at the
castle in ten minutes, my king.
Reports tell me
that the present king
is nothing more than a
bleeding heart peace-lover.
[laughs]
It's the sentimental ones
who are always
my favorite to destroy.
Don't you agree?
Oh, yes, uh...
[laughs nervously]
My reign over this planet
is close at hand.
With my ascension I shall
create a magnificent kingdom
in my own image.
[laughing]
However, before I can rebuild,
I must first tear down!
I'd like the honor
of being the first
to give my
sincere congratulations
to our new ruler.
I would also like
to remind his majesty
of our agreement that upon
his conquest of the world
I would get a piece of it.
We discussed some
marshlands earlier,
but given our successful coup,
I'd like to renegotiate.
Well! As you wish.
Piano, go down to the operating
room and take the wheel.
Send our other guests up here.
I am most grateful, sire.
[SHU, MAI gasp]
Might I inquire which
part of the world is mine?
As much...
Huh?
As much as you can
carry on the way down.
You have such humor, sire. What
do you mean "on the way down"?
Isn't is obvious? We're having
a falling out, literally.
But, your majesty, please! This
is a terrible misunderstanding!
We've worked so hard for you.
Don't forget, I'm the one
who brought you back to life!
I'm your savior!
You're nothing but an inept
clown surrounded by amateurs.
Say goodbye.
No, no please!
Give me another chance!
I'm begging you!
Please, sire, please!
Quit sniveling. You're the
one who wanted renegotiate.
[all whimpering in fear]
Ya know,
I'm really good at windows.
[yelling]
[YAJIROBE] Okay, we're here,
wherever here is.
Funny, this doesn't
look like a place
where they'd
have some good food.
Don't worry. Everything's fine.
Nothing's changed.
It's Goku!
Upa!
Goku!
Good to see you!
It's been a long time.
How have you been, Upa?
You've gotten taller.
Yes!
Father! Father! Come quick!
Goku is here to visit us!
Just remember,
you promised this visit
would include a lot of food.
Don't worry.
Oh, Goku!
Bora!
It's good to see you,
old friend.
[SHU]
Are we there yet?
From here on, I think
we should choose our allies
with more scrutiny, sire.
Be quiet!
It begins.
Let rise the flames of chaos.
Scorch the earth 'til
all I see withers and dies!
[laughing]
[NARRATOR] With restored youth
and limitless power,
King Piccolo sets out
to conquer the world.
Can anyone oppose
his reign of evil?
What fate awaits
Goku and his allies?
Don't miss the next unbelievable
adventure of Dragon Ball!