Run.
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball...
Goku found himself in hot
pursuit of a bionic bird
stuffed with
Emperor Pilaf and his crew.
Pilaf was well equipped for
battle this time
with his brand new
transforming Power Suits.
As Goku neared,
Pilaf provided a demonstration
of his deadly invention!
But fortune changed hands as
Goku returned the projectile
to its rightful owner
[GOKU] Can I please have your
Dragon Ball now, mister?
Take it...
Please take it...
[laughs]
One more thing...
Huh?
[NARRATOR] So with a quick
costume change,
Goku was off to Baba's house
with the last Dragon Ball!
Upa has an important wish
for the Eternal Dragon!
I got it!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU thinking]
I can't wait to tell Upa!
[laughs]
[GOKU] Hey, I got it!
I got the last ball!
Look, you guys!
Goku's finally back!
[gasping]
It seems his trip
was successful!
[UPA] Is that really it?
The last ball?
So you did find it!
That's right!
[chuckles]
What happened to the clothes
you were wearing before?
[laughs]
[YAMCHA] Hey, uh,
tell us about your trip!
Who was in the car?
I'll tell you about it later.
Ready?
You bet!
Now that we've got all of
the Dragon Balls,
it's time to go get
your Dad back!
[UPA] Uh-huh!
[BOTH laugh]
Sorry, Nimbus.
We don't have time
to rest just yet!
Come on up and hold on tight.
This thing goes pretty fast!
The faster, the better!
Okay, I'll be back as
soon as we get Bora home
where he belongs!
Thank you!
I'll never forget you guys!
We'll miss you!
Now you mind your father, boy.
I won't ever disobey him again.
[PUAR sniffles]
Let's go.
[sniffs]
Okay!
Hmm...
[GOKU] See ya soon!
That boy should learn
the art of taking a break!
It's so unfair; I wanted to
see the Eternal Dragon, too.
I always said
he was a tough kid,
but I still can't believe
he actually got
all seven Dragon Balls!
He certainly is amazing.
And the entire world will know
his name someday...
Huh? Now what is that
supposed to mean?
What do you know, Baba?
Just a feeling.
I sense that he'll be
a great hero of his time.
Whoa...
I thought he already was...
[UPA thinking]
Goku really did it!
It won't be long now, Father!
[BULMA hums]
So how far
can you spit, then?
Bwah!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[ROSHI] I've hit
a mosquito with a spitball
right in his eye!
[BOTH laugh]
[ROSHI] Hmm...?
Huh?
Excuse me, Master Roshi?
Hey, Yamcha,
why such a long face?
I've been thinking
a lot, and, uh...
I was wondering if you could
take me on as a student.
[BULMA] Hm?!
[YAMCHA] I think living in
the city is making me soft,
and I see what a good job
you did with Goku...
So, uh, what d'ya say?
Yamcha?
[ROSHI] Mm-mm. No way...
I'm sorry son, but
two students is my limit...
I'm an old man,
I can't handle any more.
Come on! I won't be
any trouble, I promise!
It's too much work...
[BULMA growls]
I don't see why you
can't just give him a chance!
You're nothing but a lazy,
selfish, mean old grouch!
[ROSHI] I'm not lazy... I
happen to have things to do!
If you let Yamcha
come train with you,
maybe I'll come visit, too.
[ROSHI gasps]
Your place is by the water,
and I have this new bikini
I'm dying to try out.
Well... When can you start?
[groaning]
Um... Goku?
What is it?
Is... this really...
going to work?
Don't worry so much.
Everything will work out.
You can trust
the Eternal Dragon.
[laughs]
[UPA grunts]
[UPA] Faster, Goku, faster!
[GOKU] Wow! Look at
those giant leaves!
[UPA] They're so pretty!
Can we get closer? Please?
[GOKU] Sure! Why not?
[BOTH laugh]
[GOKU yells]
[UPA laughs]
[GOKU] Watch this, Upa!
[GOKU laughs]
[UPA] I got you!
[BOTH laugh]
Whee!
[GOKU] Be careful, Upa!
[UPA laughs]
[GOKU] Hang on!
[GOKU] Hold your breath!
[BOTH laugh]
Huh?
[GOKU laughs]
[BOTH laugh]
[UPA] Are we almost there yet?
[GOKU] You're really excited,
aren't you?
[UPA] I've never seen so many
clouds! 5d
[laughs]
[GOKU] Open your eyes!
You've got to see this!
--[UPA] What?
--[GOKU] It's like a big tunnel!
[GOKU] Whee!
[laughs]
[UPA yells]
[UPA] It sure is windy
way up here!
[GOKU] I think it's refreshing!
[GOKU] So, what's the first
thing you want to say to your
dad?de
[UPA] That I love him!de
[BOTH] Yeah!
[GOKU] We're here!
There's Korin's Tower!
And that's father's grave
right over there.
I see.
[UPA wails]
[UPA] Father!
[UPA sobs]
Don't cry. He'll be
back in no time!
Yes, I know!
Wow...
Are you ready
to call the dragon, Upa?
O... kay...
Eternal Dragon!
I have a wish!
[UPA whimpers]
[UPA gasps]
[GOKU gasps]
I think it's working.
[UPA wails]
[UPA whimpers]
[UPA screams]
It's so bright!
[GOKU gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
I... didn't know
it'd be this big!
That thing's gonna
bring my Dad back?
[ETERNAL DRAGON growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU] Whoa...
[ETERNAL DRAGON] Why have you
disturbed my slumber?
Oh! He seems mad...
[GOKU] Upa, tell him your wish!
[UPA] Um, okay.
[whimpers]
[screams]
Hey... tell him.
Tell him your wish!
But... but...
[ETERNAL DRAGON]
Speak up, human!
[whimpers]
I'll tell him.
[UPA groans]
--Hey, Dragon--
--Wait, I can do it!
[ETERNAL DRAGON growls]
Help me, please.
Will you bring my father
back to life for me?
I really miss him a lot...
[ETERNAL DRAGON growls]
[whimpers]
[GOKU] So... can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Your wish is granted.
[GOKU] See?
I told you there was
nothing to worry about.
He just seems a little scary!
[UPA] Mm-hmm.
Look!
Oh! I hope he's all right!
[ETERNAL DRAGON growls]
[UPA] Ooh...
[UPA gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Fa...
Father...
[UPA laughs]
[UPA] Father, you're back!
You're really back!
[sobbing]
I missed you!
I love you so much!
[laughs]
I can't believe
you're finally home!
I thought I'd never
see you again!
But here you are! Alive!
Huh...?
[UPA sobs]
[laughs]
[UPA laughs]
I see... I think I remember...
Yes, Father...
You were dead, but Goku got the
big dragon to bring you back!
Then I owe great thanks to you.
Your wish has been fulfilled.
I will take my leave.
Now where is number four?
There it is.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[UPA] Goku, are you okay?
Why did you do that?
I knew the Dragon Balls
would get scattered
all over the world right
after the wish was made.
I had to get Grandpa's Four-Star
Ball before I lost it.
--But look at it!
--Huh?
What happened?
After the Dragon appears,
the balls become regular
stones for one whole year.
That way no one can find them
and the Dragon can rest.
Ohh!
Goku, I do not know
how to thank you!
You just did, silly!
Someday, I will find a
way to repay you.
If you ever need help,
please come find me.
Father, Goku made it to
the top of Korin Tower.
Not only that, he beat that
bad man who hurt you, too!
Ahh! You are a gift
from the stars, young man.
I better go.
What? You're going already?
Are you sure
you don't want to stay?
I'll prepare a feast.
Thanks, but my friends
are waiting for me.
Okay.
See ya later, alright?
Sure!
Nimbus!
Bye, Upa! Bye, Bora!
Farewell, my friend!
Be careful!
Come see us!
[laughs]
[UPA] Goku!
Bye!
--Bye!
--[GOKU chuckles]
[BORA] Son, are you
going to grow up
as strong as Goku someday?
Yeah!
Father?
Yes?
I'm gonna climb Korin Tower
just like he did.
If I work as hard as he does...
and practice climbing
every day...
then someday I will
make it to the top!
I'm sure of it!
Whu... Who-Whoa!
[laughs]
He's back! Look, it's Goku!
[GOKU] Hello!
What's up? Did the
Eternal Dragon help Upa's dad?
Oh yeah, it was a piece of cake!
Yay! Good job!
I bet they were really
happy to see each other!
Yeah!
You did good, kid.
[laughs]
[GOKU gasps, yells]
I gotta go!
That was a long trip!
Oh, hurry, hurry!
No! You can't do that here!
Go find a bush, you animal!
--[yelling continues]
--And he's going to famous?
[BABA] Think about the
poor creatures...
Well...
Oh, boy, what a relief!
After all this time,
you finally collected
all the Dragon Balls!
It's a tough break that
you have to wait a whole year
before you can find your
Grandpa's keepsake again,
isn't it?
Wait. [grunts]
No, I caught the Four-Star Ball
before it had a
chance to fly off!
That must have been
one nice catch!
[KRILLIN] Does this mean
you won't be looking
for the Dragon Balls any more?
That's right!
I think I'll start training
for the next martial arts
tournament now!
That reminds me--guess what?
I'm training, too! With you
guys, under Master Roshi!
He agreed to take me
as his student!
We'll have so much fun!
Yeah, I want a complete
training refresher,
right from the beginning!
I guess that's okay...
Just don't pick up
any of his bad habits.
Goku doesn't--oh wait.
You're talking about me,
aren't you?
[GOKU] That's great! Master,
we can train together, right?
[ROSHI] That's a bad idea.
Huh?
You're already
exceptionally well trained.
Don't you want to try
to grow stronger now?
Sure, of course I want
to get stronger, Master.
Then I can be of no more
use to you, son.
You've officially
outgrown my teachings.
It's time for you to set
out on your own,
and learn from the
adventure of life!
There are many things to be seen
in this vast world,
and they can only be truly
experienced in person!
Go wander, my boy,
and keep your eyes peeled.
There are endless opportunities
out there for you!
[thinking] I'm so good,
I suprise myself sometimes...
You lost me. Can you start over?
[ROSHI gasps]
--[KRILLIN chuckles]
--I mean, go travel!
[KRILLIN laughs]
If you say so!
Right.
We'll plan to meet up at the
next world tournament.
We definitely won't miss that.
Wait!
You're saying we won't see
Goku again for five years?!
No, in three years!
The tournament has added
so many participants
that they're holding it
every three years from now on.
It's a deal!
I promise I'll meet you guys
at the tournament gates!
That's so long...
Couldn't we have a reunion
sometime before the tournament?
Don't worry. The time will fly!
I'll be so much stronger
in the ring next time
that you won't even
recognize me!
[GOKU] Listen to Master Roshi,
and you're sure to get better!
Promise us you'll
be careful out there!
[GOKU] Mmkay!
Do you think three years
is enough time
--for you to get happy?
--[BULMA growls]
What're you trying to say?!
Know what?
I'll be a lot taller
by the time I see you again!
Maybe even taller than you!
[GOKU laughs]
I wouldn't count on that.
I'll grow too, you know?
I guess I'll be on my way now.
Bye, Master Roshi; Bye, Baba.
Take care, kid.
I hope you learn a lot
on this journey!
--Nim--
--No cloud! Just feet.
You won't get any stronger
if you rely on help
outside yourself!
Walk, run, swim--Do whatever it
takes to get around on your own!
What?!
I'm supposed to travel
the world on foot?!
[ALL gasping]
That's pretty harsh!
What sort of mess have
I gotten myself into here?
[whimpers]
Hmm...
That's okay!
See ya!
[GOKU laughs]
He's... just as crazy as ever...
I don't think he even
knows what pain is!
[KRILLIN] I wonder how
much stronger he'll be
after three years of this?
[ROSHI] There's
no use in guessing
when it comes to
a kid like Goku!
How about for kicks you
give them a taste
of what it's like to be Goku?
[ROSHI giggles]
[ROSHI] Okay! We've
had enough R &amp; R!
Let's race all the way home!
Loser washes my socks!
[ALL scream]
[BULMA] Hey!
I'm not your student!
I shouldn't have to
be doing this!
[GOKU] One... two...
one... two...
[chanting continues]
[NARRATOR] With the Dragon Balls
scattered across the land,
and Upa reunited
with his father,
it's time for Goku
to go back to his training.
It's only three short years
until the next World
Martial Arts Tournament.
Can Goku improve his skills
without Master Roshi?
Find out as the saga continues,
next time on Dragon Ball!