[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball...
Goku and Colonel Silver lost
the Five-Star ball to
a couple of crafty chimps.
Soldier, your rifle!
[NARRATOR] Silver's plan
to stop the fleeing duo misfired
and sent the monkeys--along
with the ball--
careening over a cliff...
Goku raced to the rescue,
and saved the monkeys by a tail.
He's escaped the fall, but
can he escape Colonel Silver?
Get me that ball! Move it!
[frustrated growl]
[GOKU laughing]
Stop it! That tickles!
Hey! That hurts!
It's been lots of fun,
but I think I should go
find Grandpa's Dragon Ball.
Bye!
[happy monkey noises]
Hmmm...
Huh?
Hm...
Well, just one.
Hey!
Oh, it's raining!
[rumbling]
Looks like the search
will have to wait.
[SOLDIER A] Attention soldiers:
all personnel
report immediately
to sector F7048.
I repeat, all personnel
discontinue search and
report to sector F7048.
Heeey!
[STAFF OFFICER]
The Dragon Ball has shifted
to a new location.
Coordinate QX2-SE.
X marks the spot.
[STAFF OFFICER] You are
to resume your search
at first light tomorrow.
Understood.
[SILVER] With the
river flooding like this,
the Dragon Ball
could very easily
be washed up on land.
Looks like I'll have to widen
the search in the morning.
Look alive men!
No cracks, no crevices,
no rocks unturned!
See ya later!
Thanks again!
Bye-bye!
[GOKU] Hmm...
Not much farther now...
I see... They haven't
found it yet, either.
Heh, heh!
They're way, way off!
[COWBOY] Oh, my aching back!
[WOLF] Yeah... and
I could really use a nap!
[gunshots]
Colonel, we were just, uh...
...takin' a break?
I have no patience for excuses.
Get back to work, now!
Yes, Sir!
[COWBOY] Man, what does he
think we are-bloodhounds?
That darn ball
could be anywhere.
This place is huge!
[WOLF] I hear ya.
It's crazy!
And he'll kill us if we
can't find the stupid thing.
[GOKU] Hi, there!
It's around here somewhere...
I'll have to narrow
it down on the radar.
[GOKU] Got it!
Hey, kid, what are you doin'?
He's too nosy!
Hey, boy!
You gotta get out of here...
We've got important work to do.
Uhhh... Ah-ha!
Huh?
Hmmm... Aww!
Too many stars...
This one isn't my grandpa's...
It's the Dragon Ball!
Yeah, but my grandpa's
has four stars on it.
This one's got five!
[WOLF] Who is this kid?
I mean, we've been
looking out here all day!
How'd he find it so fast?
Pure luck, that's how he did it.
But I'd say we're
the lucky ones now...
Hey! Why don't you hand that
to me, boy? Heh heh heh...
But what do you want it for?
I don't need any sass...
Just do as I say...
Give me that ball, right now!
You try and make me!
Nyaaah!
I'll make you all right!
No!
Well, this isn't
my grandpa's Ball,
but I'm only one star off...
The next one'll be his,
I just know it!
Sir, Colonel Silver, Sir...
I-I think we have
a problem here.
[SILVER] What is it?
Is it the ball?
[SILVER] There...!
That must be it...
You again!
You blew up my nimbus!
[SILVER] Pity.
It looks like you
lost your ride...
There won't be any
getting away this time.
[GOKU] Oh! Nimbus!
You! What did
you do to my Nimbus?!
That was a gift to me from
my teacher Master Roshi!
Why did you do that?
[SILVER]
I'll ask the questions here.
Now tell me, what do you
want with the Dragon Ball?
And how did you
manage to find so easily
what my entire army could not?
Allow me to
venture a theory here.
Our Dragon Radar
is somewhat imprecise...
Could it be that
you have something
a bit more--sophisticated?
Nyah! Nyah! I'm not
telling you anything
after what you did to Nimbus!
Say you're sorry!
Foolish...
[SILVER] You would be wise
to be reasonable, little man.
I strongly recommend
you answer,
because I'm not
going to ask again...
Tell me, why are you
searching for the Dragon Balls,
and what sort of
technology do you have
I won't say,
unless you apologize!
Now I'm leaving.
What do we have in here?
I bet it's not playthings.
None of your business!
You shouldn't take
other people's stuff.
Ah-hh...
Ahah, you're no
ordinary boy, are you?
[SILVER] No matter, I'll just
have to keep my eye on you.
But I always get what I'm after.
[SILVER] Now hand over
that sack, or prepare to die.
You don't scare me!
Just try and take it!
He... kicks like... a donkey!
You're not going anywhere...
Except to your grave!
[GOKU] Well, he won't
bother me anymore.
Oh, Nimbus,
how am I gonna get
anywhere without you...?
I dunno...
There's got to be
something I can use...
[GOKU] Hey! Maybe they've
got some capsules in here!
Jack pot!
Hmm... Now, let's see here...
Which one is the flying cloud?
I'll just try them
all until I find it.
[ROBOT] At your service.
Who are you?
You're strange...
[ROBOT] I am a multi-duty,
personal robotic assistant.
Wow! I've never seen one before.
[ROBOT] How may I assist you?
Uh, well, I really
need to go that way.
[ROBOT] Then go that way.
[GOKU] I would,
but I have to go really far,
and I don't have
anything to ride on.
[ROBOT] Throw the
Dyno-Cap labeled number 3.
Hmm... This...?
[ROBOT] Correct.
Whoa!
That's a plane!
I don't know how to fly it!
[ROBOT] I am
programmed to operate it.
Yay! Away we go!
They're still at it!
[GOKU] This isn't as
fast as the flying nimbus.
[ROBOT] Nimbus?
I do not compute.
[KUMA] Commander!
There's something very strange
happening on the Dragon Radar.
[KUMA] The Dragon Ball!
It's begun moving again!
The one Silver has
been searching for.
Unless I'm mistaken,
it's headed straight for
General White's position.
[RED] Contact Colonel Silver.
Brr! Why is it so cold?
[ROBOT] I am a robot.
I do not sense heat or cold.
You're lucky!
I'm freezing! Ah-ah-choo!
[beeping]
[panting]
Colonel Silver here.
[STAFF OFFICER] Silver!
How did the ball
get away from you?
Were you attacked?
[muffled static]
How many of them are there?
Who's responsible for this?
[very muffled]
A boy!
Huh?!
What do you mean, a boy?
Who do you think it is?
[RED] I don't know--but if
he was able to beat Silver...
We will have to be
on our guard, I think.
Colonel Silver said
he was a young child.
He can't possibly be any trouble
for an entire army of men.
[RED] You had better be right.
Get in touch with
General White at once.
Tell him to kill the boy
and bring me the ball.
Of course, sir.
[RED] And another thing...
Sir?
Bring me that
weakling Colonel Silver!
I never knew...
it could be this cold...
[ROBOT] Extreme cold is
typical of the northern region.
I wish I had brought
some more clothes...
[ROBOT] Humans are
inefficient creatures...
You are too sensitive
to external temperature...
We need to land...
it's time to land!
Hey, are you listening?
[GOKU] Hello! Robot!
Land the plane!
[ROBOT] Cir-cuits
fro-zen... fro-zen...
Oh no! We're gonna crash!
Aaaaah!!
[SOLDIER B]
Hey! Did you hear that?
[SOLDIER B] Yeah...
Sounded like something crashed.
Let's go check it out!
[RED] That's no excuse, Silver.
Please, commander.
Give me one more chance.
I'll find him!
[RED] There are no second
chances in this army.
You know that.
But Sir,
you don't understand.
The child was
exceptionally skilled...
He must have been trained.
[RED] You truly
are a disgrace...
Take him out of my sight!
Don't touch me!
]What? There's a plane down?
It's got to be the
missing jet headquarters
radioed about!
Do you have a visual?
[SOLDIER B] Yes, sir.
It's definitely one of ours.
It's here in front of me...
in pieces.
[WHITE]
According to the report,
there was a boy
flying that plane.
[SOLDIER B] There's no
sign of him here, sir.
Just a shattered robot.
[WHITE] He's out
there somewhere.
Find him!
That boy is carrying
one of the Dragon Balls!
[SOLDIER B] Yes, sir!
Over and out.
[WHITE] Hmm...
Whoever this kid is...
He's in for a big surprise!
[SOLDIER C]
Hey, I think I got something!
[SOLDIER B] What is it?
Show me.
Look at this!
[NARRATOR] Once again,
Goku has managed to escape
the clutches of the
Red Ribbon Army--
but who is this
mysterious young girl
that now has our
hero by the ankles?
Has Goku been
pulled from one danger
and dragged right into another?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!