[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
the sacred land of
Korin was visited
by the cruel Mercenary Tao,
sent to destroy Goku for
the Red Ribbon Army.
Bora, friend to Goku and sworn
protector of his people's land,
challenged the
invader... and lost,
leaving his son Upa, and Goku,
to face this
awesome threat alone.
[GOKU] That's it!
Me... Ha... Me...
Haaaa!
[TAO grunts]
Dodon Ray!
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] His task
seemingly accomplished,
Tao stole the
Dragon Balls and fled.
[UPA] Goku! You're alive!
[GOKU groans]
Wait! Upa!
If I can collect all of the
Dragon Balls
I think I can bring your
father back to life!
[NARRATOR] Now, in order
achieve his goal,
Goku has begun the climb up the
impossibly high Korin Tower,
hoping to attain
the Sacred Water.
According to legend, this
enchanted drink will
greatly increase the strength
of whoever consumes it.
But no one knows
this for certain,
for no one has ever
made it to the top...
[GOKU gasps]
I sure hope that's it...
Oohh...
Go... Don't stop...
Almost... there!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU sighs]
I made it... I'm finally here...
[GOKU gasps]
[bells jingle]
Now where is that water?
Maybe it's hidden somewhere.
Huhh...
Is it in here?
[BULMA hums]
[GOKU] Bulma!
Hang on,
I'm almost done!
Wait a second,
can she hear me?
Bulma!
Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Huh?
Stop that!
What?
Bulma! I'm up here!
I must be losing my mind.
[BULMA screams]
[GOKU laughs]
She's so silly!
What happened to
all the water?
It just disappeared!
What's in this one?
[GOKU gasps]
[CHICHI hums]
Hey, Chi-Chi!
It's me, Goku!
Hey! That's me!
[CHI-CHI gasps]
But how can I be there if I'm
right here? Wait, I remember.
[CHI-CHI] I didn't
think this day would...
[GOKU] That's when
I visited the Ox-King!
It already happened!
[CHI-CHI] You big joker!
[GOKU sneezes]
Unbelievable!
[GOKU] I wonder
who's in this one.
Huuh...?
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunts]
Whoaaa...
Weird... What was
that all about?
[VOICE] Relax, kid.
Don't stress out.
You just had
a vision, that's all.
The big three:
Past, present and future.
Hello? Who is it?
Where are you?
[VOICE] I can barely
hear you. Come on up.
I wasn't at the top after all.
The Sacred Water
must be up here.
Okay, I'm here.
Where are you?
Hello?
[VOICE] Well, alright.
It's about time
you joined the party.
[GOKU] Party...?
Come on, show yourself.
[VOICE laughs]
[VOICE] Take the
blinders off, babe.
I'm right here.
You're pretty spry
for a kid your size.
I enjoyed your climb.
[GOKU growls]
Look, I'm not here
to play games.
I need the water.
[CAT] Come closer.
My name is Goku.
I'm here for the Sacred Water.
Can you help me?
Like I haven't heard
that one before.
[GOKU growls]
What's your name?
Korin... Keeper of the Tower.
Korin?! Then you have
the Sacred Water?
[KORIN] Of course.
We're surrounded
by sacred water.
Every drop on this planet.
[KORIN laughs]
I need it. That's why I'm here.
I was told that if
I climbed this tower,
I would find water that
would make me stronger.
Please, it's important.
Ah, and what would you
do with this strength?
I would use it
to help my friends.
That's a noble
statement for a child.
[GOKU] What does my age
have to do with it?
[KORIN] Ask me again
when you're older...
Look, kid, no hard feelings.
It's just not your time.
No, wait!
I climbed the tower.
Now please give me a drink.
That is the rule... right?
Are you certain the
Sacred Water is what you need?
[GOKU] Mm-hmm.
Is that... from your heart?
Yes, sir.
I... say no.
[GOKU] What?!
[KORIN laughs]
[CHILDREN laugh]
[CROWD murmurs]
[CHILD] Mommy, what is it?
What does it say? Mommy?
[WOMAN] It says the twentieth
anniversary campaign of the...
Oh dear, the killer!
That's Tao. Now's
your chance... do it.
[rifle fires]
[CLIENT yells]
[GUNMAN wails]
[CLIENT whimpers]
[GUNMAN screams]
Everything is arranged
as you ordered, sir!
Welcome back, sir.
The refreshments are in the room
and your bath is being drawn.
Excellent.
[TAO yells]
[TAO] Boil five minutes...
Then crack and serve.
I hope Goku makes
it to the top safely.
He's all I have left...
I don't understand.
Why did you waste my time?
I didn't even get to see it!
[KORIN laughs]
You mean the Sacred Water
that's on top the fountain?
Huh?
But-But I thought,
I mean, you said, it-it...
[KORIN] Ugh. If you're done
falling all over yourself,
maybe we
could continue.
Why do you want more strength?
Oh, see I've been collecting
the Dragon Balls
and that's how I met Bora.
He gave me the Four-Star Ball.
And then he was
killed by this mean--
Yeah, alright, alright.
Easy on the speech, okay?
You're hard on the ears.
Don't talk? But you asked me to.
Just lock your jaw
for a minute, would ya?
You have to defeat Tao
the Mercenary to retrieve
your Dragon Balls and then
collect the other three
so you can wish Upa's
father back to life.
Is that the gist of it?
What?! How could you
know all of that
when I didn't even say
anything about it?!
I--read--minds.
But don't worry, kid, there
weren't that many chapters.
Aahh...
Amazing!
Thanks, but you're
an easy audience.
Pure minds are like
looking through glass.
So it's alright then?
Don't worry, I'll get it.
This is great!
I can't wait to see
how strong it makes me!
How does it look up there?
[GOKU gasps]
Fine. I've got it.
[KORIN] Are you sure?
No problem.
Haaah!
[GOKU yells]
You said I could have
the Sacred Water!
If that's what I said,
then don't mind me.
Have all you want...
Go on. What are you waiting for?
Okay. Then I'll try again.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU growls]
What's the big idea?!
You said I could
drink... Didn't you?
That's right...
If you can get around me.
Alright, then. Two can
play at that game!
--Look!
--[KORIN] Hm?
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU whimpers]
Not that this isn't any fun,
but before you play the game,
maybe you should
read the directions.
[GOKU growls]
[KORIN] Come on.
It's right here...
Keep your eyes on the prize.
You liar! I'm gonna get
that bottle! Count on it!
You hear me?!
[KORIN] Come on! O-Oh!
It's getting heavy.
[GOKU yells]
[KORIN laughs]
[GOKU grunts]
[KORIN] I understand
if you want to give up.
No hard feelings!
[KORIN laughs]
[BOTH yell]
[KORIN] Wuh-oh!
[GOKU grunts]
[KORIN chuckles]
[GOKU growls]
[KORIN laughs]
[GOKU pants]
You're too fast.
I can't catch you.
That's right, if you
keep that attitude.
You can't retrieve what
your mind can't conceive.
Get it? All you're
doing is reacting to me.
Learn to anticipate your
opponent's actions.
Okay.
[GOKU grunts,
KORIN laughs]
[KORIN] Be careful!
[KORIN laughs]
[BULMA] Oh no!
Everything's getting wet!
Huh...?
Master Roshi!
Are you coming inside?
Oh, you go on in.
Don't worry about me.
These old bones need a workout.
[thunder rumbles]
Something's brewing up there.
I haven't seen a storm
like this since...
[KORIN] You can't be that tired.
Come on. We're just
getting started.
[GOKU] Korin, tell me, has there
ever been anyone
who was able to climb the tower
and get the bottle from you?
Yes. But only one,
about 300 years ago.
Exactly how old
are you anyway?
Eight hundred years.
Give or take a few.
Eight hundred years?!
Oh, wow. You're really old!
[KORIN] Show some respect.
I'll tell you something else...
The only person who ever
succeeded in drinking
the sacred water...
...was the man you call Master.
Wait--What?! Wh-What
are you saying?!
[ROSHI yells]
Judging by the way you move,
I'd say... your teacher is
the old turtle-hermit, Roshi.
You mean Master Roshi, my Master
Roshi climbed this tower...?
Is that how he became so strong,
by drinking the sacred water?
[KORIN] Mm-hmm.
That's right.
Whoaa...
I can't believe Master Roshi
was the first one here!
Believe it or not, it's true.
He was a tricky one.
Why do you say that?
Was he really fast?
How long did it take him
to get the bottle from you?
Whoa! Just three minutes?!
No, sir. Three years.
Th-Three years?!
[GOKU groans]
[NARRATOR] If it took
Master Roshi three years
to get the Sacred Water,
how long will it take Goku?
Let's hope he brought a snack.
Tune in next time, for another
exciting episode of Dragon Ball!