[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
King Piccolo began his
invasion of the world
in the most unlikely of places,
King's Castle,
a symbol of peace,
which the conqueror
reduced to pieces.
[NARRATOR] In an instant,
King Furry's entire kingdom
was transformed into
a barren wasteland.
[NARRATOR]
Declaring himself ruler,
Piccolo promised more death
and destruction if King Furry
did not comply with his demands.
After an exhaustive journey,
Goku and Yajirobe finally made
it to the top of Korin's Tower.
Master Korin was surprised
to learn of Goku's desire
to undertake
additional training,
and advised his pupil that
engaging King Piccolo
in further conflict would
result in his own demise.
[STAFF gasps]
[PIANO] Do you really think King
Piccolo would ever be satisfied
with this slop?!
[STAFF gasps]
You will prepare a new
menu with all haste!
Dishes of newt manure, deep
fried eyes, fresh moose pie,
with dinosaur tongue
and brain pudding.
[PIANO] You will prepare 111
of each dish within the hour.
Everything must be in order
when sire awakens from his nap.
[PICCOLO snoring]
[KORIN mumbling inaudibly]
Ultra Divine?
That's right. This water
is most certainly divine.
But, Master Korin,
how is it any different
than the Sacred Water
I drank a long time ago?
Actually, there is
a huge difference.
You see, Sacred Water is
merely water with a kick.
No magic in it. Ha.
But Ultra Divine water is packed
with mystical properties
and a magical zing!
Whoa! If I drink
Ultra Divine Water,
then I'll be super strong! Hey!
Come on, Master, give me some
of the Ultra Divine Water!
Please, Master! Please, please!
Enough! Some things
never change.
You're just as hasty as ever!
I can't help it, Master.
You said I'd be stronger
if I drink it.
[KORIN] The water would increase
your abilities, that's true.
But to enjoy its benefits,
you would first
have to track it down.
Huh?
[KORIN] It is a perilous
journey. Far to the north,
there is a treacherous
maze of ice.
To obtain the water,
you must first navigate
through this icy labyrinth.
The liquid is hidden
somewhere in the cave.
[GOKU]
A maze? What's that?
[KORIN] It's a complicated
network of passageways,
with many confusing routes to
choose from, but only one exit.
It's easy enough to get in.
The trick is getting out.
Once inside the labyrinth,
it's easy to get lost.
You can find yourself
wandering aimlessly for weeks,
or even years!
Many brave explorers have
attempted to navigate this path,
only to never be
heard from again.
Now that you know the peril
involved, what will you do?
Do you still wish to seek it?
Mm! Sure do! I'm not
afraid of the maze.
I must find the
Ultra Divine Water!
You'll go with me,
won't you, Yajirobe?
You've got to be
kidding. No way!
You won't?
Of course not! Why in the
world would I voluntarily
go to such a terrible place?!
You're crazy!
Count me out of this one!
Hey! Where are you going?
Downstairs. See ya.
[door slams]
[YAJIROBE]
Ultra Divine Water! I'm hungry.
I could use a snack.
Now, where would that old cat
store his food?
I don't see any--
That pot looks a
bit suspicious...
I'll bet he's got some nice
tasty morsels hidden in there!
Huh?
What's that? I can't make
it out, but it's cold.
Maybe it's ice cream!
[GOKU] And I don't have
the Nimbus Cloud with me.
How long will it take me
to get to the northern
part of the world?
[KORIN] As long as it takes
you to hop into that pot.
[GOKU] Oh, I get it.
That pot's like a door, right?
[KORIN]
A very special door.
Thanks, Master Korin.
I'll see you when I get back.
If you go, there's one
thing you must avoid.
Darkness.
Don't worry. I've never
feared the dark before.
You will. It'll be
your greatest challenge.
This darkness is
blacker than night.
It veils the Ultra Divine Water
in illusion so cunning,
you may never escape its
empty void, once ensnared.
I'll keep that in mind.
[yelps]
[yells]
[yelping]
[groaning]
Am I there yet?
[KORIN]
Hey, Goku!
Here! No, no! Up here! Look up!
If you find the water,
return to this exact spot
and I'll pull you back up again.
Right. Well, see ya later!
The days of impetuous youth.
[neck pops]
I'm glad that I'm old.
Yajirobe! I forgot. Yoo-hoo!
Yajirobe! I got some fudge!
Oh!
It's freezing in here!
But it doesn't look
as bad as I thought.
In fact, I can see
a path up ahead.
[GOKU gasps]
Yajirobe!
You said you weren't coming.
Did you change your mind?
[YAJIROBE]
Huh?
I didn't have a choice.
Did you fall in by mistake?
You could say that.
See ya. I'm goin' back up.
I wish you could stay.
I'd like some company.
Wait up!
It's too cold in here.
If I stay much longer,
I'll turn into an ice cube!
Listen Yajirobe--
[YAJIROBE] Don't try to
talk me out of this, Goku.
What I do is none
of your business.
[GOKU] But the pot's in
the other direction.
[YAJIROBE]
Eh?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
I'm not getting stuck in
an ice maze for anybody!
I don't even like cold food!
[YAJIROBE] Are you sure
we're going the right way?
Huh?
Someone sure picked a
funny place for a monument.
[GOKU]
Hm...
That's strange.
What's strange is
I don't remember
passing these on the way in.
Are you sure you know
where we're headed?
Stupid ice!
[YAJIROBE yelps]
Huh?
I don't know his story,
but if we stick around here,
we're gonna end up like him!
Right.
[YAJIROBE]
Let's go!
What did that?
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH yelp]
[YAJIROBE]
Wh-What's going on?!
[YAJIROBE] I've got a bad
feeling about this!
[SNOW BEAST roars]
[SNOW BEAST growls]
It's a-an ice monster!
[GOKU, YAJIROBE grunting]
Why do you fight us?!
[roars]
Were you sent here by darkness?!
[SNOW BEAST growls]
[GOKU, YAJIROBE grunting]
[growls]
Time to make some ice cubes!
You're gonna be sorry you
messed with Yajirobe!
That's just impossible!
[GOKU gasps]
[gasps]
[grunting]
Take that!
[SNOW BEAST growls, roars]
It didn't phase him at all.
He's too strong.
[SNOW BEAST growls]
[YAJIROBE]
What now?
I got it! Ka... Me...
Ha... Me... Ha!
[roars]
[DARKNESS groans]
[DARKNESS] Who dares wake
me from my cold slumber?
It is human. It will suffer.
They will all suffer who
trespass on my domain.
We won!
[yelps]
Goodbye!
--[YAJIROBE, GOKU panting]
--[SNOW BEAST groaning]
[YAJIROBE] My Senzu Beans!
I can't leave them!
[GOKU]
Yajirobe, come on! Ah!
[SNOW BEAST growls]
[GOKU, YAJIROBE grunt]
[SNOW BEAST roars]
[GOKU, YAJIROBE yelp]
[GOKU, YAJIROBE groaning]
[YAJIROBE, GOKU scream]
Grandma...?
Hold on... hold on.
Thank you... I never expected
kindness from a stranger...
Your help makes
the end bearable.
Don't say such a thing!
Never give up on hope.
Yes. There is hope.
I see it in your eyes.
--[bang]
--[gasps]
[GUARD groans]
Like I was saying before
we were interrupted, sire,
the cooks are
completely inadequate.
They can't even perform
the simplest of tasks.
[PICCOLO]
Then eliminate them all.
Things taste better
from scratch.
Murderer.
[heartbeat pounding]
Huh?!
What a moron.
[TIEN grunting]
[TIEN yells]
[pants, growls]
I failed!
[grunting]
What is this place? Where
are we? Yajirobe! Yajirobe!
Wake up! Yajirobe!
Come on, wake up!
Wake up, Yajirobe! Get up!
Come on! Come on! Ah!
[YAJIROBE groans]
[YAJIROBE] Ow! What's the
big idea?! That's cold!
Wow! That was great!
We escaped the snow beast,
thanks to you!
I haven't gone that fast
since I last rode my Nimbus.
Too bad you can't fly.
[YAJIROBE] Would you be quiet!
What are you thanking me for?
It wasn't like I had a choice!
Is there a sign on me that
says passengers welcome?!
[DARKNESS] Humans have
disturbed my slumber.
They trespass at
their own peril.
Sorry you feel bad, but thanks.
[YAJIROBE]
Whatever. Now look where we are!
We'll never find the pot down
here! And it's all your fault!
Okay, then we'll head
for the water!
[YAJIROBE] No way! I'm going
to find my way home!
And that's that!
[DARKNESS growls]
[DARKNESS] It's time we
call upon our visitors.
[DARKNESS cackles]
[ROSHI]
Yes, sir.
[NARRATOR]
Has Master Roshi returned?!
What other sensational mysteries
lurk in the darkness?
And what peril will they
bring Goku and Yajirobe?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!