[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku overcame the pain
Piccolo inflicted on him,
and threw everything he had at
his out-of-control opponent.
[GOKU] It's time for
your terror to end!
[NARRATOR] It was a showdown
between two fierce warriors,
and it was clear that only
one of them would survive!
Luckily, Goku summoned
enough strength to bring
the curtain down on Piccolo.
[GOKU]
I won.
I did it!
[NARRATOR]
Goku scored a direct hit,
finally ending
Piccolo's spree of terror.
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU]
Hello?
[ALL]
Oh, Goku!
[NARRATOR] Even though he
was exhausted from battle,
Goku had no time to waste.
He had to retrieve
his Power Pole
so that he could climb to
Kami's temple in the sky,
in the hope that Kami
would revive his friends
that Piccolo had
pummeled into oblivion.
But one question remains:
Can Goku convince
Kami to help him?
[GOKU laughs]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[GOKU]
I found the Power Pole!
Boy, that didn't take very long.
This is just an example
of Kami's will at work.
[panting]
Good work.
Soon you'll be ready
to meet Kami.
Let's go!
I'm ready to go
right this minute.
Fine. Then I'll meet you on
the roof with your Power Pole.
Sure!
[GOKU laughs]
[groaning]
[YAJIROBE screams]
[YAJIROBE groans, cries]
Now, take the Power Pole,
and put it in the hole
in the roof top there.
[GOKU]
Okay.
Now hold on to the pole, and it
will take you to the temple.
So, like this?
Yes, that's it.
Now command your pole to stretch
and you'll be on your way.
I see. So it's like
an elevator, isn't it?
Ah, ah!
I want you to take
this bell with you.
What's this for?
Only a person with
that bell can meet Kami.
Uh, okay.
[bell rings]
I'm all set. Get ready.
Here I come, Kami.
[YAJIROBE]
Uh, wait a minute.
You're going to meet
Kami dressed like that?
Your clothes are all torn up.
You should show
him some respect.
New clothes?
Nah, don't worry. Your new
clothes would get worn out, too.
[GOKU, YAJIROBE gasp]
What do you mean by that?
Are you trying to say I'll have
to fight Kami when
I get up there?
Oh no, of course not.
Kami's very gentle.
What exactly do you mean?
Oh, you'll see. [chuckles]
Oh, don't worry
about it, it's safe.
[GOKU]
Uh...
[KORIN] It'll all make
sense when you meet Kami.
Now go, go. Be on your way.
Come on. Can't you be
a little more specific?
That's okay! I'm still going.
Great, and good luck!
You're gonna need it.
See ya.
Um, okay. Here I go.
Goku, watch yourself,
and make sure you don't fall.
Power Pole, extend!
[GOKU]
See you when I get back!
[GOKU chuckles]
Sometimes, I wonder if
he's afraid of anything.
Don't know. I gave up trying to
figure him out a long time ago.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
I hope he'll be
all right up there.
[GOKU thinking]
Master Roshi, Krillin, Chaiotzu,
this is for you.
I'll be seeing you again soon.
I just know it.
[LAUNCH] That does it.
You're back in one piece again.
It's a good thing you're
in excellent shape, Tien.
Ya should heal fast.
Thanks, but your
kindness helps a lot.
Stop. There's no
need to flatter me.
[OOLONG]
Hey, what about me?
Huh?
I sure wish I had a girl
who looked like you,
and wanted to take
care of me all day.
[BOTH]
Uh...
Oh my. I made you guys blush.
[LAUNCH growls]
Pig, shut it!
Don't make me get tough!
Quit squirming,
--and stand still.
--[OOLONG yells]
[TV REPORTER] And now a special
announcement from the king,
to the boy who defeated
Piccolo and saved the world.
You are to receive the Blue
Star Medal for your bravery.
Hey, he's talking about Goku.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
If you're out there young man,
please come and
collect your medal
at your earliest convenience,
for what you have done.
The citizens of Eastern City
owe you our deepest gratitude.
Wow! The Blue Star Medal.
Hey, isn't that the highest
honor in the whole world?
I hope that he
shows up to get it!
I just hope that wherever
he is, he's not in trouble.
I remember he said
something about meeting Kami.
If that's true, I wonder
how he's going to do it?
[door bell rings]
Great! That could be Goku.
[REPORTERS chatter]
Stay right there, you!
[REPORTER whimpers]
Sorry. W-We just wanted to talk
to the boy who beat Piccolo.
[REPORTER B] Yeah, he's a hero
and I want to get an exclusive.
What exactly is your
relation to the little boy?
Care to make a
statement at this time?
[REPORTER C]
How old is the boy?
[REPORTER D]
Have you known him very long?
Wow. Who woulda thought
that a kid like Goku
could ever become
such a big star?
[WOMEN giggle]
Goku! Goku. Goku!
[OOLONG sighs]
Lucky guy. I'm so jealous.
[chuckles]
[REPORTER C] Come on, let's
have a look at the kid already!
[REPORTER B] Are you hiding
him somewhere in the house?
Uh... I don't know
where he is right now.
[OOLONG]
Hi! What's goin' on everybody?
[ALL gasp]
It's Goku?
Goku?
[REPORTER B] Did you
have any special training?
Hi! My name's Goku!
Mr. Goku, everyone's
dying to know about
the battle you had with Piccolo.
Care to comment?
Well, before I do...
What is it?
[groans]
How about a kiss?!
[REPORTERS groan]
What?
[BOTH]
Uh.
Mm-hm.
Yeah, come on, give me
a big kiss, sweetie!
Let's go. What're
you waiting for?
[OOLONG groans]
Oh, my head hurts.
Oolong!
That does it! Let's squash him!
[REPORTER A]
Get some pictures of this.
What? Oh, no.
[GOKU yelps]
[screams]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU screaming]
[FAMILY laughing]
My, what a special
birthday boy you are.
I hope this has been a
very special day for you.
[BOY chuckles]
[MOTHER]
We're so proud of you, dear.
Yes, happy birthday, my dear!
Happy birthday!
Here's a present from
the both of us to you.
Wow. What could it be?
A plane!
Great, thanks a lot!
Thanks, Daddy. Thanks, Mama.
[ALL laugh]
[growls]
[glass shatters]
[BOTH gasp]
What?! Who's there?
[DOG barks]
[growling]
Very strange. It's all clear.
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[crash, glass shatters]
[ALL gasp]
[BOY]
Get him, Daddy.
Come back, you thief!
--Sic 'em boy. Go get him!
--[DOG barks]
Oh, my plane is all broken.
[DOG barks]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. gasping]
[GOKU groaning]
That must be the
temple up ahead.
Wow! It's huge.
Korin was right,
it's way up here.
[GOKU]I hope my pole
can stretch all the way.
I made it.
Uh, uh?
[GOKU]
Ah-ha!
Great, a ladder.
[YAJIROBE]
I wonder how Goku is doing?
I hope he's okay.
Hey, what kind of guy
is this Kami anyway?
[KORIN chuckles]
Come on, spit it out.
[KORIN]
Well, let's put it this way:
I'm sure Goku will be quite
surprised when he sees his face.
You mean that he's a really
scary looking person?
[KORIN]
That's right.
But Goku has seen him before.
Eh?
Mm-hm. And when he meets
Kami, he'll be surprised.
There's no doubt about that.
[GOKU grunting]
Huh?
[GOKU]
Uh?!
[birds tweet]
Hey. Hi.
Hi.
Hi. I'm Goku. I'm looking
for someone named Kami.
Ah, yes. I know Kami,
but my name is Mr. Popo.
Kami told me all about you.
You beat Piccolo, didn't you?
What? How did he
find out about that?
Kami knows about everything,
my friend. Kami is great.
So, is that Kami's
house over there?
[Popo]
Yes.
Can I meet him now?
[Popo]
Do you have proof
that Korin has approved
of your being here?
Uh?
You mean this bell?
Korin gave it to me.
--[bell rings]
--[GOKU laughs]
Good, it's clear to me that
you have been approved then.
Are you ready for the test?
Uh? What test?
The test. You must
fight me, Mr. Popo,
and if you win the match,
you will then be able
to meet Kami.
Sure, that sounds like
an easy enough thing to do.
Okay, let's have a match.
You're the first challenger
I've had in centuries.
This is exciting.
Great. So, we'll fight until
one of us gives in, okay?
Sounds great.
Ha! Have I got
a surprise for you.
Really? Please then,
go ahead. Show me.
Here I go.
[laughs]
[gasps]
He's gone.
There you are.
[GOKU groans]
Ouch! Hey!
Yes, gotcha.
Yeah, but I think that punch
was just a lucky coincidence.
[grunts]
I won't let that happen
again. Are you ready?
Always.
With this punch...
...you'll give up!
[GOKU groans]
Oh. Got you again.
[GOKU groaning]
You're not very strong.
Please, are you actually the
same guy who defeated Piccolo?
I am strong, so you
take that back!
You're weak.
[GOKU growls]
This time I'll get you.
Yes, please, come on.
[GOKU growls]
Huh? You won't beat me.
Look what you did,
you frightened the birds
away with your bad attitude.
Rrgh... Be quiet!
Don't make fun of me!
[GOKU yells]
Ah!
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU groans]
Mr. Popo is very
disappointed. Too bad.
I'm sorry, you will
not meet with Kami.
I can't believe that Korin
would even send you here.
[GOKU groans]
No! It's not over! I'll get you!
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
HA!
[belches]
[GOKU gasping]
What? I don't believe it.
He ate the Kamehameha Wave!
[GOKU grunting]
Why don't you just give up?
I'll try this one. This is
the punch that beat Piccolo.
[yells]
No way!
It's a shame that you
have such great power,
yet you make such
poor use of it.
You need to learn control,
because only then will you
be able to pass this test,
--and meet with Kami.
--[GOKU groans]
[NARRATOR]
Has Goku met his match
in the jovial Mr. Popo,
and if so, does this mean
he'll never get to meet with
Kami and save his friends?
Find out, on the
next Dragon Ball.