[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Krillin fought a vicious
vampire as the battle
for the last Dragon Ball began.
It was the first of a
five-match tournament,
pitting Goku's team
against the spooky forces
of Fortuneteller Baba...
Together, Puar and Upa
turned Krillin's defeat
into triumph as they out-foxed
their toothy challenger
for a spectacular victory.
[FANGS screams]
[GROUP cheering]
[NARRATOR] In the next match,
Yamcha was ambushed
by an invisible man.
The situation looked bleak
until Krillin exposed
the sneaky fighter with
some trickery of his own!
[YAMCHA yells,
SEE-THROUGH groans]
[NARRATOR] Yamcha scored
a second victory for his team,
but the revelry was
short-lived as the fighters
moved to a more dangerous
venue for the third match...
The Devil's Toilet.
[YAMCHA groans]
Great. Tongues for a bridge!
Why am I not surprised.
[YAMCHA]
Ew! I think I smell why
they call this the
Devil's Toilet! Phew!
[BABA cackles]
[GROUP gasps]
Look on the bright side.
These are great seats!
Would you grow up!
Yamcha's risking his life!
If you can't control
your sister,
at least show some support.
[BABA] I trust you will find
this new venue a challenge
worthy of your skill.
The tongues are your boundary.
The rest of the rules
are the same.
But like you,
the stakes are higher...
[BABA] For should you
fall into the toilet,
nothing can save you.
[YAMCHA gasps]
[BABA cackles] One drop of that
toxic soup on your skin
means instant death.
[GROUP screams]
Hm. And I thought my
plumbing was bad. Brother!
Baba... No offense...
...but you've fallen off your
crystal ball one too many times.
Your fear is understandable.
If you give up, I won't
think any less of you
than I already do.
[YAMCHA] Lady, I've never
quit anything in my life
and I'm not about to
start now. Do your worst.
[BABA cackles]
That's the spirit.
Your sister is rude,
inconsiderate and shameful.
I see the family resemblance.
Now I present to you
the third challenger.
[chanting] Rise again and
be restored once more...
[GROUP gasping]
[chanting continues] Rise again
and be restored once more...
[YAMCHA yelps]
[chanting] Rise again and
be restored once more...
[GROUP gasps]
Is this for real?!
Now that is creepy.
[chanting] Rise again and
be restored once more...
[GROUP gasps]
Rise again and be
restored once more.
[YAMCHA gulps]
Master Roshi, what is that?
That's a sarcophagus!
[GOKU]
A what?
[BULMA]
It's a coffin!
[GOKU]
Why? Does he have a cold?
Arise, my mummified warrior!
Come forth, I beseech you!
[YAMCHA gasps]
[GROUP gasps]
[BANDAGES cackling]
He's hurt? Why is
he in bandages?
It's a mummy, you dummy!
That's what it's
supposed to look like!
[BABA cackling]
[BANDAGES cackling]
[YAMCHA]
Come on.
Just once I'd like to fight
someone who's not a freak.
[BANDAGES] This little whelp
is why I've been awoken?
[BANDAGES cackles]
Pain and suffering are all
you have to look forward to now.
Ha! Whatever.
Anyone ever tell you your
mummy dresses you funny?
[BABA] That's enough chitchat.
Save it for the fight.
[BABA] The battle will continue
until one of you gives up
or is destroyed.
Let the match begin!
[YAMCHA] From the looks of him,
this guy's more about
brawn than he is about speed.
If I can keep moving
and strike fast,
he won't be able to defend
himself. Ha. I can do this.
[BANDAGES cackling]
You can do it, Yamcha!
Be careful!
[KRILLIN]
Don't you worry about it, Puar.
He's toast. That mummy doesn't
stand a chance against Yamcha.
No...
I'm afraid this monster is
different from the last two.
[KRILLIN, GOKU]
Huh?
[ROSHI] Throughout the years,
there have been
several visitors who have made
it past the first two matches,
but never the third...
No one has ever faced this mummy
and lived to tell about it.
Oh. That means he
must be super strong.
[YAMCHA yells]
[BANDAGES grunting]
[YAMCHA, BANDAGES grunting]
He's too fast!
[GROUP screams]
[GOKU]
I don't think so.
Tear him apart, Yamcha!
[BANDAGES, YAMCHA grunting]
Come on!
[BANDAGES grunts]
[YAMCHA groans]
[YAMCHA yelps]
[GROUP screams]
--[GROUP screaming]
--[BULMA] Yamcha!
[PUAR screams]
Hold on!
[YAMCHA grunting]
[BANDAGES cackling,
YAMCHA grunting]
[GROUP gasps]
Leave him alone!
[YAMCHA grunting]
[GROUP gasps]
[BANDAGES]
Get up. We're not finished.
I have slept too long to
end this so soon. Let's play.
[YAMCHA grunting]
[BABA cackles]
[GROUP gasps]
[ROSHI]
Hm...
[BANDAGES cackles]
[YAMCHA grunting, panting]
[BANDAGES]
Now. Stand up and face me.
Move! I want to see your
expression as you die.
[YAMCHA]
Lucky for me he's long winded.
Come on, Yamcha!
Finish him already!
Let's get this over with!
Hang in there, Yamcha!
Just stay alive!
[YAMCHA grunts]
Wolf Fang Fist!
[YAMCHA yelling]
[YAMCHA grunting]
Yay, he's doing it!
No.
[YAMCHA yells]
[YAMCHA, BANDAGES grunting]
[YAMCHA groans]
[BANDAGES yells]
[GROUP screams]
[YAMCHA screams]
No, Yamcha!
The Wolf Fang-Fist!
It didn't work!
Ahhh! He's gonna kill him!
[YAMCHA groans]
What? What?
Speak up, little man.
I can't hear you
when you're crying.
Yamcha, you can beat him!
Please get up!
Leave him alone, you big bully!
[YAMCHA grunting]
I-I can't...
[BABA cackles] So, what do you
think of old Bandages now?
Not much!
[BANDAGES groans]
You did it, Yamcha!
You beat him!
Have a nice flight.
[BANDAGES growls]
[YAMCHA]
Huh?
[BANDAGES]
Weeeeee-oh!
[YAMCHA yelps]
[GROUP gasps]
Incredible!
[BABA cackles]
[YAMCHA growls]
Let's see now, where were we?
Oh, yes! You were
about to die.
[BANDAGES cackles]
[YAMCHA grunting]
My men don't like to wait.
It makes them angry.
I do understand
your frustration, sir.
Your patience will
be rewarded shortly.
Save it. Your customer
service routine may work
on the tourists,
but I'm not buying it.
Patience, my friend.
Your turn will come... soon.
Who needs patience
when you've got muscle?
Property damage is strictly
frowned upon by management.
Your frightened words
don't fancy me!
Why I was once third runner-up
at the Wold Martial
Arts Tournament!
[BANDAGES grunts]
[crash]
[GUY 1] What's happening?
Is it an earthquake?
No. That's just management
battling our current guests,
and itsounds like
it's your turn... now.
[GROUP yelps]
I've suddenly developed
a stomachache.
Same here, but In my head.
It's contagious!
That's too bad...
Would you like me to
reschedule your appointment?
Well, I--
[GROUP yelps]
Okay, that about does it
for me. How about you guys?
[GUY 2]
Who recommended this place?
[GHOST]
Huh?
I-I-I just forgot something
that I remembered.
I don't even like
to fight. Imagine that!
I really wanna be a librarian.
Good luck to you then.
If you change your mind,
we'll still be here.
[BANDAGES, YAMCHA grunting]
[YAMCHA groans]
--[PUAR yelps]
--[BULMA] Yamcha!
[YAMCHA groans]
[GOKU growls]
Brace yourself, son.
This is going to get ugly.
[UPA] Yamcha's in trouble
and it's all my fault.
I have to do something!
[BANDAGES grunting,
YAMCHA groaning]
[UPA growling]
I'm sorry, but you
can't interfere...
Yamcha must fight alone.
I know. But he's out
there because of me.
He's risking his own life
to save my father.
[BANDAGES grunts,
YAMCHA groans]
[YAMCHA panting]
[ROSHI]
No.
The only person that
Yamcha is fighting for
right now is himself.
His pride refuses defeat.
[YAMCHA grunting]
[UPA gasps]
[YAMCHA]
I can't even...
...fight one.
How am I supposed
to handle three?
[YAMCHA grunting]
[BANDAGES]
Aw...
--[GROUP screams]
--[BULMA] Yamcha!
[BANDAGES cackles]
Stop hurting him!
That's called the
Stretching Bridge Technique.
It's Bandages' signature move.
He's such a show-off
for the crowd.
[YAMCHA grunting]
[BANDAGES]
I once made a man's head
touch his feet doing this...
He's in show business now
as the Human Pretzel.
Yamcha, give up! Let's switch!
That's right!
You've done your part.
Now let Goku take over.
Please! Stop fighting!
I... I can't!
Good. I was hoping
you'd feel that way.
[YAMCHA screaming]
[GOKU growling]
This isn't good...
I don't think Yamcha can escape.
And he's seconds away
from being crushed!
[GOKU gasps,
BULMA gasps]
This is crazy!
Wait!
No, wait Puar!
[PUAR yells]
[BANDAGES]
Huh?
[BANDAGES grunting]
[YAMCHA groans]
[PUAR groans]
[BULMA, KRILLIN scream]
Puar! Are you okay?
Say something!
Yamcha!
Puar! No!
[BANDAGES]
Huh?
[GROUP gasps]
[YAMCHA grunting,
BANDAGES chuckling]
Enough.
The stench of your weakness
is making me sick!
[YAMCHA grunting]
Now... Do you give up?
[BANDAGES]
Answer me!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[BULMA, KRILLIN yell]
I accept.
[YAMCHA groans]
[GOKU]
Power Pole extend!
[GROUP sighs]
[BABA cackles]
Your life has been spared.
But you are very much defeated.
[YAMCHA grunting]
Two words, I quit.
I suggest you look
them up sometime.
I thought Yamcha did
an exceptional job,
except for the
almost dying part.
He's unstoppable.
Nothing I did had any effect.
Not even my Wolf Fang Fist!
Don't beat yourself up, kid.
That's my sister's job.
[BABA cackles] So, are you
discussing your next fighter
or your retreat?
No shame in losing.
Everyone knows my warriors
are the best in the world.
I'm next! I'm ready to try.
Please don't fight.
It's too dangerous.
I don't want anyone else
to get hurt because of me.
Don't worry, Upa.
I won't let you down.
[YAMCHA]
Goku!
You be careful.
Thanks. I will.
We're going to
win this. I promise.
Be strong! Good luck!
[GOKU]
Thanks!
Huh?
We can start any time you want.
[BANDAGES cackles] Is that so?
And who are you supposed to be,
the half-time entertainment?
[KRILLIN] Master Roshi...
Goku is our last hope.
What do you really think
his chances are out there?
[ROSHI sighs] I doubt any mortal
man could beat this mummy.
[UPA, KRILLIN yelp]
That's not good!
Although...
With Goku's recent
increase in power,
perhaps he does possess
the strength... I hope.
Ready? You may begin.
[BANDAGES cackles]
For someone who's so mean...
you sure do like to
laugh a whole lot.
[BANDAGES cackling]
[NARRATOR] Goku is the
last defender on his team.
If he loses this match,
the location
of the last Dragon Ball,
and Upa's father,
may be lost forever.
But how can he win
against an opponent
who has never been defeated?
The answer lies
ahead on the next
spectacular episode
of Dragon Ball!