[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
The full moon was out,
and Goku transformed
into a giant, killer ape!!
Ka...
[NARRATOR] Determined to protect
all the innocent spectators
at the tournament,
Jackie Chun fired
his maximum power
Kamehameha Wave!
Ha!!!!
[NARRATOR] Yamcha tried
to stop the old master
from releasing
this deadly attack,
knowing Goku could
return to normal
if they just cut off his tail!
[NARRATOR] But it was too late.
The attack had been launched,
and the damage had been done...
And when the energy
blast cleared out,
the monstrous ape
was nowhere to be found...
What did he do to our Goku?
Goku! Oh no you can't be gone!
[NARRATOR] Is this true...?
Has the rampaging ape
really been stopped...?
Has Jackie Chun really
put Goku down for good...?
Will Bulma and the others
have to say good-bye
to their loyal friend...?
[NARRATOR] Many things
are up in the air,
but one thing is certain...!
The World Martial Arts
Tournament ends today!
On Dragon Ball.
[ANNOUNCER]
This has been a fight
for the history books,
ladies and gentlemen!
[ANNOUNCER] Wow...!
Who could have imagined
such a great end!
What... is he saying?
[BULMA sobs] Great end?
Doesn't anyone
understand what happened?
I'm... not even sure I do...
[ANNOUNCER]
And so it's been decided...!
Jackie Chun will be
the new World Champion!
He's no champion...!
He's a murderer...!
It isn't fair!
[KRILLIN] Give us Goku back!
[OOLONG] Dumb old fool!
He was our friend!
Don't you just stand there...!
Hey!! Do you hear me?!!
Say something!!!
Calm down...
Look over there.
Hey is that a--??
A tail...
And that's a naked boy...
Yay! Goku's alive!
Yamcha he made it!
Goku wasn't the target
of my Kamehameha Wave...
That was!
[ANNOUNCER]
There's nothing there!
The sky! It's been...
de-mooned! It's gone!
[CHUN] Well with the
moon destroyed it can't possibly
get full again so Goku
won't turn into a big ape!
[CHUN thinking] Sometimes
I'm so clever it amazes even me.
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Jackie Chun has done
a reprehensible thing!!!
What's going to light up
the skies for us at night...?!
What about romantic
moonlit walks?!!
And you can just say good-bye
to relaxing ocean wave CDs!!!
What about the Wolf-Man?
What will he howl at?!
Stop being a goof
and start counting!
Oh yeah, of course...
[ANNOUNCER]
One...! Two...!
Hey! I thought for sure
I was wearing clothes...
Darn you! If you
had started counting
when you were supposed
to, I would've won!
That's... funny...
[cheering]
That little guy
really had me worried.
Haha! Yeah...
He's pretty good at that.
And continue!
Whew...
Blowing up the moon can
really drain your energy...
That last attack took
a lot out of him...!
Goku! You can win!
Right!
[girls tittering]
Oh stop!!
I shouldn't
look but I am...
What's wrong, sirs?
What are you all
giggling about...?
I get it! You must be girls!
Okay on second thought,
stop fighting...!
Goku! Do you wanna get me fired?
[KRILLIN] Don't worry...!
He can borrow my suit!
I wonder if my clothes ran
away when I was sleeping...
[KRILLIN] Don't worry, I already
made a tail-hole
in the back for you...
You know, you really
freaked me out, Goku...
So what's it like
to run around as a
giant scary monster?
I don't know...
[KRILLIN] Oh... come on,
you can tell me!
I'll keep secrets!
Tell you what now?
Fine, meanie
But I know... If I could...
I'd jump on mountains...!
And make earthquakes!
[GOKU] You're strange...
[GOKU] Gee... What's wrong with
the arena...?
It looks like there
was an earthquake...
Now... Here comes
Goku to the ring...!
Wearing plenty of clothes!
[GOKU] I'm gonna wrap
this up, Mr. Jackie!
[tummy growls]
Hungry...
Unguarded!
Ka-me-ha-me...
Haaaa!!!!
[ANNOUNCER] Oooh!
What a drag for Jackie Chun!
His energy attack has fizzled
out like a flat can of soda-pop!
[CHUN]
Don't quit on me now!
I guess he doesn't
have enough energy left!
Come on.
[GOKU] And that means
he can't fly anymore either!
And that makes it easy...!
Ka... me... ha... me...
Now wait a second!
Ha!!!!
Here goes!
[panicked noises]
It worked!
Oh no!
I'm going to land
outside the ring!!!
Come on now!
Goku, you did it...!
It's a ring-out!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Jackie Chun has
landed outside of the ring!
That makes Goku the new Martial
Arts Champion of the World!
[GOKU] Yay!
Way to go!
[CHUN] Excuse me!
The fight isn't over just yet...
Look at my feet, carefully.
My... feet haven't
touched outside the ring...
Wow... Well I'll be...
[ANNOUNCER]
The fighting continues!
You sure are
a lucky fellow...
I was in control
the whole ti--time...
Your Kamehameha Wave is
too weak to do damage now.
[GOKU] It is?
I'm afraid that
your fatigue and hunger
have drained your energy past
the breaking point...
Same with me...
We've both done every fancy
trick our bodies can handle...
It looks like we'll have to rely
on good old karate chops and
flying kicks to finish this...
The strongest man
will stay standing...
It's as simple as that.
Sounds like fun to me.
Come on, Goku...
Give everything you've got...
Let's make this
finale worthwhile.
No tricks,
no fancy shows...
Right... No energy attacks...
Just fist-to-fist
martial arts...
[ANNOUNCER]
Absolutely amazing...!
Goku and Jackie Chun
have launched
into the most intense
close-combat we've seen yet...!
Such stamina!
By my watch,
they've been fighting for,
oh my gosh, over four hours!
And you can't even tell!
[ANNOUNCER] Okay...
maybe you can tell a little bit.
What a play!
Despite obvious physical
exhaustion on both sides,
neither of these fighters
is willing to give up...!
They just... keep... GOING!
[CHUN thinking]
This boy's gonna wear me out
if I don't finish him soon...!
I definitely need a knockout!
But what finishing
move can I use...?
His body's too
small for a lock...
Just a stubby torso
and short little legs...
[CHUN thinking]
Yes...! Of course!
Hey...!
How 'bout...
one final charge, Goku?
Fine!
[ANNOUNCER] This could be it!
[ANNOUNCER] You--
you saw it yourself, folks!
A double knockout...!
By the rules, I have
to start counting...!
One...! Two...! Three!
Four!
Come on Goku...!
Just stand up!
Six!
[ANNOUNCER] Seven!
Get along there,
Jackie Chun!
Goku...! Stand up!
[ANNOUNCER] Eight!
That's the spirit, kiddo!
Nine!
[ANNOUNCER] Ten!!!!
[ANNOUNCER] Neither one
of them were able to stand!
Common rules would
label this a draw...!
But the World Martial Arts
Tournament can't go
without a champion!
I believe in these
rare situations...
the first person who stands...
and says that he is the
champion becomes just that!
Huh?
So, which fighter can stand up
first and declare victory?
All you gotta do is
stand up Goku!
[ANNOUNCER] Here comes Goku...!
He's on one knee!
[ANNOUNCER]
Goku is up on both legs...!
And Jackie Chun is
still glued to the floor...!
All Goku has to do now
is say he's the champion!
I... I... am... the...
cham... pi...
[ANNOUNCER] Oh!
Goku was a mere syllable
away from winning it all!
But I'm afraid we can't
accept incomplete sentences!
Oh look!
Now Jackie Chun
will give talking a try!
I'm the world champion!!
I'm the world champion!
Yes, I am the champion!!
Hahahahahahaha!
[ANNOUNCER] Well I couldn't
have said it better myself!
Jackie Chun is the new
Champion of the World...!
And this time I'm certain of it!
[CHUN thinking]
That was a close one, Goku...
And I must admit my victory
was only due to our sizes...
My legs are longer,
so I could hit much deeper
on that last flying kick...
Sort of a cheap trick,
but it was my only chance...
And it was for your own good.
Maybe you'll thank me someday,
when you're older...
[ANNOUNCER] What a long
and crazy day it's been!
Hasn't it, folks!
Oh... Hey...
Did I win it Mr. Jackie?
No son, you didn't.
Oh... darn... I really tried...
[ANNOUNCER] Let's not forget
the twelve year-old Goku
who almost won
the whole tournament!
Wasn't he incredible?!
Wasn't he, folks?!
[ANNOUNCER] Now...!
Without further ado,
let's award Jackie Chun with his
prize as the new World Champion!
And you deserve every bit of it!
500 thousand zeni!
You were really
strong Mr. Jackie!
Yes... well you were
a worthy opponent.
I'm going to train every day
until I get as strong as you...!
And when I do will
you fight me again?
Yes... uh... of course...
You cross your heart?
Uhhh... Mm-hmm.
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
I hope you enjoyed
the tournament!
Please fly safely
on your way home
and watch out
for stray dinosaurs!
Great job Goku!
[GOKU sighs]
Yeah...
[KRILLIN] You wanna find Master
Roshi and get something to eat?!
[GOKU] Hey you bet I do!
[KRILLIN] Master Roshi!
[GOKU] Master Roshi!
[CHUN]
Huh?
[ROSHI] I go through
so much for my students...
[ROSHI] And what do
I have to show for it?
Nothing except a
truckload of prize money...!
I'm very selfless...
[ROSHI thinking]
500 thousand zeni...
Just imagine the
possibilities...
Uhhhhh.... Wha...? Uhh...
[ROSHI] Do you have a tissue?
I'm so hungry...
I've looked through
every bathroom stall
in a seven-mile radius...
[YAMCHA] Where is he?
Did... you try the lady's room?
I wonder if he even watched
Goku in the tournament?
Hu...ngry...!
[ROSHI] Yoo-hoo!
Master Roshi!
Okay, where in the
world have you been?
I wanted an autograph
from Jackie Chun,
and you wouldn't believe
how long the line was!
[KRILLIN] So did you see us
in the tournament finals,
Master Roshi?
Well of course...!
And you boys both did very
well for your first attempt!
Goku got robbed at the end...
He would've won if he
hadn't been so hungry!
[GOKU] I don't know
about that, Krillin.
Jackie was pretty strong...!
I still don't think
I could've beat him!
[ROSHI] That's for sure!
You've got lots to learn before
you're up to his level...!
And plenty of others
are just as strong...!
There's a whole dimension of
fighting techniques that YOU...
don't know yet...
[ROSHI] All training so
far has been child's play...
The real stuff is yet to come!
[BOTH] Right!
[ROSHI thinking] I should start
recording my
speeches and sell them...
Now what do you say we
all go out to dinner
and celebrate our first
successful tournament!
[GOKU] Ooh! Can we really??
Would you four like
to come with us?
Sure!
Oh, yeah!!
Alright, but if you
make one crude remark
I swear I'll break your arm.
[GOKU] Hey! Hey!
Can we eat now?!
[rapid eating sounds]
Can I get some pepper?
Yeah...
[GOKU] I sure was hungry!
He... just ate 57
full-course meals...!
Really...? I lost count
around forty...
Can I have another
bowl please?
I think you've had
enough for one day...
Yeah... You're right...
I should probably
save room for desert!
It's... four hundred and
seventy thousand zeni, sir.
But... that's all my...
prize... money!
[NARRATOR] Looks like Goku
got to spend the prize
money after all...!
And so, the long journey to the
World Martial Arts tournament
has come to a close...!
But trouble is already brewing
over the horizon,
and the next exciting
adventure is soon to come!