[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[GOKU grunting,
SOLDIERS groaning]
[RED groans]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU screams]
[STAFF OFFICER screams]
[NARRATOR]
After single-handedly destroying
the Red Ribbon Army,
Goku found himself
in possession of
six Dragon Balls.
To their surprise,
Bulma and the others found
there was little to do besides
congratulate the tiny hero
on his amazing accomplishment.
[BULMA]
Evil Army Defeated By Child.
It's just one army!
[NARRATOR] With only one
Dragon Ball left to find,
Goku followed his friends
back to Roshi's Island
so that Bulma could
repair the Dragon Radar.
[ROSHI grunting]
[BULMA]
I don't get it.
It should be working just fine.
But it won't show where
the last Dragon Ball is.
Maybe the ball is so far away
that it's out of
the radar's range.
If it's in this universe,
my radar can find it.
Up until just a while ago,
I could see all seven balls.
Uh, unless...
If the Dragon Ball was
swallowed by something,
that could explain
why we can't see it.
Uh, swallowed?
You mean like... eaten?
[BULMA]
It's a possibility...
Living tissue could
disrupt the Dragon Balls
unique electric wave,
making it virtually impossible
for the radar to detect.
Who'd eat a Dragon Ball? Because
it's probably bad for the teeth.
There are certain animals
that will eat anything.
But, something probably
swallowed it by mistake.
So you're saying that,
if something did eat the ball,
there's no way to find it?
That's right.
Without a clear signal,
I don't see how we can do it.
[GOKU yelps]
But I have to find it, and fast.
Cheer up. Maybe that radar's
just a piece of junk!
[BULMA growls]
I don't design junk!
We can't give up.
[PUAR, BULMA gasp]
[ALL sigh]
[ROSHI humming, grunting]
Oh! I have to find a way
to get the last ball.
[GOKU]
I can't stop now.
Upa's counting on me
to wish his father back.
[ROSHI] Eh-hem. You could
visit Fortuneteller Baba.
Her clairvoyant powers
would be more than enough
to find the seventh ball.
--[ALL] Huh?
--Who is Fortuneteller Baba?
Who!
Is that a friend
of yours, Master Roshi?
Whenever I can't find something
I've lost or misplaced,
I pay a visit to
Fortuneteller Baba's Palace.
[ROSHI yelps]
She always has the answer.
That's great! So, how
do you get to her palace?!
[ROSHI] Let's see now.
According to the map,
Fortuneteller Baba's
exact location
should be right about...
There! There it is!
This is a nice picture,
but how's it going to help?
It's a map, silly. You read it.
Of course, it would help if
we could understand the writing.
It's kinda weird, isn't it?
That must be the
symbol of a lake.
[YAMCHA] Huh. From the
west valley it's about...
...14 miles.
Alright! That's it!
We know where it is.
I'll go with you, Goku.
[ALL gasp]
[KRILLIN] Sounds like
an adventure! Count me in!
Me too!
Thanks. Let's go!
[YAMCHA] Alright, all aboard.
Next stop is Baba's place!
Yamcha, I need you to
give me a plane capsule.
I've decided it's time
I've gone back home.
What's up? Don't you
wanna go with us?
It'll be fun.
Fun! Is that what
you're calling it?
Well, no thank you!
I've had just about all the fun
I can stand for one lifetime!
Oolong? You're coming, right?
[OOLONG screams]
What do you think I am, crazy?!
Huh?
One thing's certain. This should
be some great training.
[ROSHI]
Good. You need it.
[GOKU]
Bye, bye!
Get me a souvenir!
Take care! Don't train too hard.
I dunno why they were afraid.
Who knows. I guess
we're just a rare breed.
Not everyone can stand living
life on the edge the way we do.
[PUAR]
Right, Yamcha?
Yeah, sure.
Master Roshi didn't tell us
much about this Baba character.
Wonder what she's like.
If Master Roshi knows her,
I'm sure she's nice.
He would have told us
if she was dangerous.
You got a good point there.
[PUAR] I guess there's
a first time for everything!
[YAMCHA, GOKU, PUAR laughing]
[ROSHI]
Hm...
They'll be fine. But still...
I should have
told them everything.
[LAUNCH grumbles]
[PUAR sighs,
YAMCHA, GOKU, KRILLIN laughing]
[KRILLIN, YAMCHA, GOKU sigh,
PUAR giggles]
[PINK BELLE] And so I told him,
if I wasn't meant to have it,
it wouldn't have been on sale!
[BLUE BELLE]
Polyester is timeless.
Corn... But Korin is a cat.
Maybe it'd be funnier
if I didn't know him.
It's just a play on words.
You know, Korin sounds
like corn. That's the joke.
Sorry, Puar. I don't get it.
Look! Ice cream!
[YAMCHA, PUAR gasp]
[KRILLIN yelps]
[GOKU gasps]
Aw...
Goku!
Your clothes are tearing,
like, real bad!
Aw. Boy, I guess they got
worn-out with all the fighting.
Hmph. You're sloppy.
Well, I guess it's time
we bought you a new outfit.
I doubt this Fortuneteller Baba
would even let you
in the door while
you're lookin' like that.
[KRILLIN, PUAR] While you're
at it, buy some underpants!
Wah! Oh, okay. But I
hope they fit this well.
[PUAR, KRILLIN, YAMCHA giggling]
[GOKU grumbles]
This stuff itches.
What would you prefer?
I'd like to have my
old clothes back, okay?
Hm. I believe that I could
make you a new suit
using the old pattern.
Definitely a wise idea!
[BOTH laughing]
And would you like to keep
the same symbol?
Yes. I want the same letters
on the front and back.
Ooh, also, will you please
make a hole for my tail?
Of course.
Do you know about how
long this is gonna take?
A design this simple
shouldn't take me too long.
A couple of hours.
Oh, and, sir?
[SHOPKEEPER]
Hm?
I got ten zenis for ya if you
can get it done in an hour.
Um... Sure. Sure.
[YAMCHA] So, seems we've
got some time to kill.
You wanna grab a bite to eat?
Good idea!
[GOKU laughs] Sounds great.
But I'd rather take this time
to go get Upa.
[GOKU]
This way he won't be alone,
and he can go with us
to find the last Dragon Ball.
It won't take me long!
Sure, why not. Sounds like
a good idea to me.
Nimbus!
[GOKU giggles]
Hey! Don't forget
your way back!
We're leaving in an hour!
[GOKU]
Okay!
I'm here!
[GOKU]
Upa!
Upa! Are you home?!
It's me, Goku!
Up--
Hm? Go-Goku?
[GOKU giggles]
Upa!
Yay!
[UPA giggling]
I'm back!
[UPA]
Goku!
I've missed you!
Me too! Guess what,
I've got great news!
[UPA gasps] Tell me! Goku, did
you get all the Dragon Balls?!
No, but I'm close.
Just one more ball
and I'll have all seven.
Then I can ask
the Eternal Dragon
to bring back your father.
He'll... come home?
Yep, I promise!
[UPA]
Thank you!
You wanna take
a ride on the Nimbus?
[UPA]
Sure!
Your cloud is fast.
How far are we going?
We're going to meet my friends
and then we'll head out
to find the last Dragon Ball.
Goku, I've never been
away from home before.
I'm scared.
I know. New things are scary.
Like leaving home for
the first time or broccoli.
[GOKU]
But it gets easier.
But wait. I didn't tell my
father why I was leaving.
He'll understand. Besides,
the next time you see him,
you can tell him face-to-face.
That's true!
[GOKU, UPA giggling]
Guys, this is Upa.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Hey.
Hi there. I'm Puar.
Hi. Nice feather.
Goku, here's your
new uniform... Enjoy.
[GOKU giggles]
Uh, ha-cha!
Uh... huh?
Upa's coy, but I
think she likes me!
You are a boy, right?
Yes.
Oh! I was joking... Ha ha.
Huh?
Ya know, lately it's
been a lot easier
to tell the difference
between a boy and a girl.
Goku! You don't change
clothes in the street!
[BELLES giggle]
[BOTH]
Put your clothes on right now!
[GOKU giggles]
Thanks a lot, Yamcha!
Come on, let's fly.
We're so high! This flying
machine's fantastic!
[GOKU giggles]
Hm. Rough ride ahead.
[PUAR gasps]
[YAMCHA] Puar, please tell me
we're getting close.
[PUAR] It should be
around here somewhere.
I can't see a thing.
[UPA] Hey, those look
like Korin's Tower.
Only they're black and moving.
Rats!
Yamcha... What are those?
[YAMCHA]
Huh?
[YAMCHA screams]
[ALL screaming]
Go!
[PUAR whimpering]
[UPA screaming]
[KRILLIN]
Has anybody seen my--
Seat belt?!
I think my eyes are stuck.
[KRILLIN grunting] Hey! I think
I see a lake down there...
...with a building!
[PUAR]
You're right! I can see it too.
[YAMCHA]
Let's go!
Hey, check it out!
It looks just like the map.
We made it!
[UPA]
This place is very strange.
[KRILLIN]
And popular, by the looks of it.
Check out the crowd.
Hi.
Yeah, what?
[YAMCHA nervously laughs]
Nice w-weather...
Welcome. Now get
in line. Quickly!
Formation before information,
as I always say.
Hi. Is this
Fortune Caller Baba's house?
Teller, Fortuneteller.
And it's a palace, not a house.
[GHOST]
Ok! Are you five together?
Uh, yes. Yes we are.
[GHOST giggles]
Good, good. Marvelous.
Just wait here until
I call you. Enjoy the view.
[GOKU]
Uh...
What was that?
Judging from the
size of those guys,
I think this lady's name
should be Fortune-wrestler Baba!
If this gets ugly,
I want ya to know
I'm behind you. Way behind you!
In fact, I'll be in the
airplane waiting to take off.
[GENTLEMAN]
Uncanny!
I should have known the diamond
necklace was behind the bar.
[WIFE] Sarah will be so relieved
to have it returned to her.
[GENTLEMAN]
Yes.
Now she can join her sisters
at the yacht club,
and we will have a
happy pooch once more.
All thanks to Baba!
[engine revs]
[KRILLIN] They were
normal looking, anyway.
I'm sure we'll be fine.
Hm...
[GHOST]
Alright, next group, follow me.
Remember, everyone
stay together.
Victory will be ours!
[FIGHTERS murmuring]
Those guys acted like
they were heading into battle.
Yeah!
Does anyone else have
a bad feeling about this?
[FIGHTERS yelling]
[ALL gasp]
[FIGHTERS groaning]
[UPA whimpers]
It doesn't sound like
they're having fun.
[FIGHTERS screaming]
[ALL gasp]
[OCTOPUS grunting]
[FIGHTERS groaning]
[YAMCHA, KRILLIN gasp]
[GHOST giggles]
Heal quickly! Come back soon!
[FIGHTERS]
Huh?
[FIGHTERS scream]
Uh... Thank you for your
patience. Follow me, please.
[ALL gasp, whimper]
Wait. What happened to them?
Why were they all banged up?
[GHOST giggles]
Let's go.
[GOKU] Huh?
[PUAR whimpers]
[GHOST]
Hurry now. Don't dawdle.
[UPA]
This is too dangerous.
I-I'm not scared.
[PUAR]
Ya-Yamcha?
Behold, Fortuneteller Baba!
[BABA]
Good.
[KRILLIN, UPA whimper]
Oh my, you've brought
me young ones this time.
[PUAR, UPA, YAMCHA,
KRILLIN whimper]
So you're Fortune Seller Baba?
[BABA grunts]
Fortuneteller Baba.
That's a funny name.
It's foreboding and mysterious!
Okay.
Can you help us find
something we're looking for?
Certainly. What is
lost, I can find.
[GOKU giggles]
Yes! This is perfect!
Ya know, for being
such a creepy lady,
she sure is kinda nice.
Of course, there is
a small fee for my trouble.
Oh, how much do you
charge to tell fortunes?
Before taxes,
and with our coupon...
It will run you roughly,
around 10,000,000 zeni.
[ALL]
What?! 10,000,000 zeni?!
What's the matter?
Is that a lot?
I beg your pardon, ma'am,
but-but we don't have
that much money!
Don't you fret, young man.
We have an alternate
method of payment.
[BABA chuckles]
Come along. Follow Baba.
Hey wait! Where are we going?
[KRILLIN]
I don't like this, Yamcha.
[YAMCHA] Just be prepared
to run on my signal.
Here's how it works.
Your group will do
battle with my fighters.
One on one.
[ALL gasp]
[BABA]
If your team member wins,
they will move on
to the next match.
If they lose, another in your
team will resume the battle.
This will continue
until one side wins.
If you defeat all
five of my fighters,
I will tell your
fortune for free.
[GOKU laughs]
[KRILLIN] Oh!
Is that it? Piece o' cake!
Fighting is what we do.
We're practically experts!
You don't know who
you're dealing with.
Three of us have
actually participated
in the World
Martial Arts Tournament--
very successfully, I might add.
So your crew should
be no problem.
Well! Guess I'm in
the presence of greatness!
I shall strive to make this
challenge worthy of your skills.
[BABA cackles]
[NARRATOR] Who are these
five mysterious fighters
that Fortuneteller Baba
plans to pit against
Goku and his friends?
Judging from the last team,
our heroes could be
in grave danger.
Find out next time,
on another thrilling
episode of Dragon Ball!