Hyahh!
[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball:
Goku launched a single-handed
assault on Muscle Tower
that brought him face-to-face
with the deadly
Major Metallitron.
This monstrous agent
of the Red Ribbon Army
fought like a
one-man killing machine
as he attempted to
terminate our little hero.
And as Goku soon discovered,
a machine is
exactly what he was!
That's right--
the Major was a robot!
And with the firepower
of a small army at his disposal,
this metallic menace
kept Goku hopping
as he tried to bash, smash
and crash his way to victory.
The situation grew more
desperate by the minute,
but as Goku prepared to fire a
final Kamehameha blast...
... the bionic bully
ran out of steam.
Hmm. Looks like someone forgot
to charge their batteries.
Is it really over?
[MURASAKI]
Augh!
Luck is not a skill,
but this child has plenty of it.
Murasaki...
Eliminate this
nuisance immediately!
Aye!
The end is near, little lamb.
[WHITE] They call him
a messenger of death;
swift as the wind,
and utterly lethal.
You will not see or hear him,
but he is there.
He strikes without warning.
If you happen to catch
a glimpse of his silhouette,
then you are already dead.
Those foolish enough to
resist him pay a terrible price.
And now, little lamb,
he is coming after you.
[SUNO] Good spirits, watch
over Goku and keep him safe.
Hello? Is anybody there?
Well if you are,
I hope you're ready!
[yelling]
'Cause here I come!
Wha--What is this place?
It's so dark.
Hey, what--
It feels like a rock...
Who put that in the
middle of the floor?!
[GOKU]
Is that a...
It almost looks like they've
got a whole forest in here.
Why would someone
wanna plant trees inside?
I wish there was some light
so I could see better.
Wow, this is--
Whoa!
Who is that?
Hey, who's there?
Show yourself!
[MURASAKI] You are trespassing
on private property.
You are the first
person to ever reach
the fourth floor of
Muscle Tower uninvited.
I am here to make sure
you are also the last.
Who are you?
And where are you?
[MURASAKI]
I am a messenger of death.
The great ninja Murasaki.
The only time
you will see me
is just before
your final breath!
[laughing maniacally]
[GOKU]
He's close. I can feel it.
But where?
Hi-ya!
[MURASAKI]
You little brat!
Whew! That was close!
[MURASAKI] You weren't
supposed to dodge that!
[GOKU] Okay, it's my turn!
Show yourself!
Right now!
[MURASAKI]
You dare to challenge me?!
So be it!
[MURASAKI]
Ah, what's the matter?
You can't find me?
Try to keep up!
[MURASAKI]
Haha!
Haha! Hoho!
[MURASAKI]
Hohoho!
Hahaha!
[MURASAKI making
taunting noises]
[taunting continues]
Yah!
[thumping noise]
What's this?
[incoherent babbling]
Hey, did you drop this?
Give that back!
Give it to me right now!
Give it! Now! Now! Now!
It's mine!
Give it--Give it back to me!
Mine! Mine!
Is that what you call
showing my sisters the sights?!
You thief!
This is my personal property!
Have you no shame?
Are you trying to ruin me?
No... you can keep it.
Thank you...
[coughing]
What did you do that for?
[MURASAKI]
Ha! You think you are so clever.
Fool!
You have only seen
what I have allowed.
But now you shall see nothing.
I am invisible!
Yes, feel my power!
I am as transparent
as cellophane!
Tremble!
For I am as the warm wind blows,
silent but deadly!
Uhh... I see you.
[MURASAKI] Impossible!
You are delirious with fear!
[GOKU]
But you're behind the flag.
[MURASAKI] Huh?
I told Mother to
put the tree pattern
on both sides!
Here, you see?
Now I am invisible! Haha!
[GOKU laughs awkwardly]
It's official...
He's a complete moron.
So you saw through
my simple disguise.
Good... Now we can get on
to more important matters.
Go to the tree and count,
and I will show you a trick
beyond your imagination.
So we're going
to play a game?
Ninjas don't play games!
Understand?
This is a highly
complicated maneuver!
What's it called?
It's... classified.
Go to a tree, count to 30,
and try to find me!
Okay. I guess I can do that.
[GOKU]
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten...
...thirteen,
fourteen, fifteen...
[GOKU] ...eighteen, nineteen...
[GOKU] ...twenty-three,
twenty-four, twenty-five...
Twe--
Uh... twe--uh...
Hey, what comes
after twenty-five?
Don't turn around!
Keep your eyes shut!
I am dealing
with powerful forces,
which your tiny little
mind cannot possibly fathom!
To become the rock
requires privacy!
That means no peeking!
Wow, is the rock empty inside?
Intolerable!
How can you hope to
comprehend the way of the Ninja
when you can't even count
past number twenty-five?!
You are unworthy of my time!
Learn to count!
I know how to count...
I only get stuck
on that one number...
Twenty-three,
twenty-four, twenty-five...
Then comes twenty-six!
Good. Now save your
counting for the tree.
And this time, be sure
to keep your eyes closed
until you have recited
all thirty numbers!
If you forget your place,
then make something up.
I don't care,
just keep counting, okay?!
Okay, okay, I understand.
[GOKU] One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine...
[GOKU] Twenty-six, twenty-seven,
twenty-eight,
twenty-nine, thirty!
Peek-a-boo, where are you?
Knock knock, open up!
Hope he's not down there.
Hello?
[GOKU] Knock-knock, open up!
[strange breathing noise]
Where's that coming from?
[strange breathing
noise continues]
[MURASAKI]
He'll never find me down here.
I am incognito.
I am like the fish.
Clever as the shark.
I am one with the water.
Hey! Go away, frog!
[gurgling]
[pained sputtering]
[GOKU laughing]
Tag! You're it!
What's the matter with you?!
Are you crazy?!
Just look at my tongue!
Look what you did to me,
you savage monkey boy!
That was a dirty trick!
But don't worry--
I'll pay you back.
Do you want me to hide
while you count this time?
I am done with
such child's play!
Witness the ninja's speed!
Follow me, little tortoise.
Just try to
keep up with my dust!
Uh... uh...
[laughing tauntingly]
Oh, a race!
This'll be fun! Yipee!
You fool!
No one can match my speed!
No one!
He's getting closer!
Time to slow down, boy!
Oww! Owowow!
I guess you get
the point, huh? Ha!
Never follow in the
footsteps of a ninja!
[laughing]
[MURASAKI laughing]
I'm back!
You nuisance!
[GOKU laughing smugly]
You--You little brat!
You will suffer for this!
Moron... He is a moron...
Why me?
[WHITE]
Get to work, Sergeant Major!
Do your job!
Kill him! Kill him now!
Yes, sir.
I will not fail you.
The boy will die...
...immediately.
My blade will
see to that. Oho!
Now no more games.
Okay.
Oblivion... awaits you.
Who's that?
Is he on the next floor?
Enough talk!
My sword, once drawn,
has never known defeat.
Can you say the same
thing about your stick?!
Here!
[pained screaming]
[pained screaming continues]
Now you have a tail!
Just like mine!
[pained screaming]
[pained screaming continues]
[laughing]
[screaming continues]
I'm gonna need my pole back!
[incoherent babbling]
[laughing]
You... will pay
dearly... for this...
Can we break for a snack soon?
My favorite sword!
What have you done?!
Sorry, but nothing
can beat my Power Pole.
Can we eat now?
I am unarmed.
Will you not fight me
with your bare hands?
Okay. Sure.
[MURASAKI] What great
confidence you have in yourself.
Wahh!
That wasn't fair!
You said you
didn't have a weapon!
You really are a fool!
This is a match
of life or death.
Who said anything
about being fair?
You lied.
You're not a very nice person.
Wahh!
[MURASAKI]
Ohohohoho! Ahahahaha!
Good! Well played.
The outcome... satisfactory.
Game over! I win!
[NARRATOR] Has the
unthinkable happened?
Has Goku fallen victim
to Murasaki's deception?
Or is he just playing dead?
If he is down for the count,
things don't look good
for Suno's peaceful village.
For without Goku to stop him,
General White can once again
use the destructive force
of Muscle Tower to make good
on all of his
dastardly intentions.
And what of
the Village Chief,
locked somewhere
high atop the fortress?
Who will rescue him?
If Goku can't do it, no one can.
There are many
questions to be answered,
but one thing is certain:
With our hero at the mercy of
the diabolical Red Ribbon Army,
no one is safe.
On the next danger-filled
episode of Dragon Ball!