[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
After discovering
the Bansho fan,
Goku and ChiChi returned
to the Ox King's castle
to battle the mysterious fire
which had threatened
to consume the entire kingdom.
Using the power
of the Bansho fan,
Goku created a massive wind,
strong enough to
blow out any flame.
ChiChi and the villagers
watched in awe
as Goku's efforts seemed
to extinguish the blaze.
However, the end
was far from over,
as the fire continued to
rage with increased fury.
The plan had failed.
Hope gave way to fear
as the villagers watched
their town burn.
And ChiChi's desperate attempt
to save her father
seemed in vain.
[CHICHI]
Papa!
You... are... going... out!
[grunting]
[CHICHI]
Oh... Papa.
[yells]
[BABA]
Goku, stop! Don't use the fan!
Wait a minute!
[screams]
Huh?
Uh?
Baba, what's wrong?
[BABA] The Bansho fan has no
effect on these flames
because this fire was forged
in the magical furnace.
Magical what?
All you're doing
by waving that fan
is making the flames stronger.
What should I do? Watch?
[BABA mumbling]
Hmm... hmm.
[BABA]
Behold, the magical furnace.
It's shaped like an octagon.
The clue was about the furnace!
[BABA]
Yes. In fact, the Bansho fan
was originally used
to create fire for the furnace.
But there has to be some
way we can put it out!
There's always a way, but the
peril is beyond imagination.
You must journey to Mt. Five
Elements and find Tajoro.
Tajoro... Is that
some kind of monster?
He's many things, including
the keeper of the furnace.
[GOKU sighs]
Well, if this Tajoro can help us
save the Ox King,
it's worth the risk.
Tell me how to get there.
Watch the crystal ball.
This is the entrance,
the Gate of the Five Elements,
located on Frying Pan Plain.
It's on the other side
of the world.
[BOTH]
The other side?
[BABA}
If you embark on this quest,
do so with the knowledge
that you may not return.
The path you must travel
is not an easy one.
It is fraught with
dangers both seen and not.
Mt. Five Elements is home to
more than just the furnace.
It is also the gateway
to the dark world.
[CHICHI]
The dark world?
[BABA] It is where the shadow
souls dwell, the home of evil.
Only in spirit form can the
journey be made successfully.
[GOKU] You mean we can't get
there without dying?
If you could,
you'd be the first.
It is said that the foot
of the mountain
is guarded by warrior spirits,
barbaric assassins who destroy
any living creature
that approaches the barrier.
So you see, the trick
isn't how to get in,
but how to get in alive.
[CHICHI]
Just once, couldn't it be easy?
[BABA laughs]
It looks like we're
getting close.
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[OX KING] You sent them
to Mt. Five Elements?!
Old woman, are you insane?
They'll be killed!
And by the looks of it,
they won't be the only ones.
Anyway, it was their
decision. I warned them.
ChiChi... Goku...
It looked smaller
in the crystal.
Are you ready?
Yes.
[GOKU grunting]
I've never seen a road
like that before.
Stay on your guard, ChiChi.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not afraid of monsters.
[gasps]
But I do fear sharp spikes.
Uh-oh.
Hey, I know!
We can use your cloud.
Huh? Right! Nimbus!
--[CHICHI] Huh?
--Where is it? Flying Nimbus!
[GOKU]
Flying Nimbus!
It must not wanna go near
the mountain. We're on our own.
What can we do?
We'll have to jump.
[GOKU grunting]
Come on! It's no problem!
[CHICHI] Tell me that
when I'm on the other side!
[CHICHI screams]
No!
[screaming]
[GOKU grunts]
Whew!
[CHICHI screams]
[sighs]
[CHICHI] Okay, I take it back.
I am afraid of monsters!
Ah!
Goku, what now?
[CHICHI] Oh, no.
I think we're in trouble.
Shadowy figures in mist
can't be good!
Can't we... just talk?
[DEMON]
You are not welcome here. Leave!
We don't want any trouble.
We've come to see Tajoro.
[DEMON A]
Leave now or be destroyed!
I had a feeling you'd
say something like that.
[DEMON]
You will not enter the mountain.
Try and stop me!
[screams]
[GOKU grunting]
No!
You won't get rid
of me that easily!
Fine!
[DEMON A]
Foolish mortal.
[yelling]
[gasps]
[DEMON A]
Die!
[screams]
Uh?
I'm trapped!
Goku!
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU screams]
[screams]
[DEMONS laugh]
Goku!
[GOKU]
They're strong...
But so am I.
Let's see you avoid this!
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
Ha!
You did it!
[screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[CHICHI screams]
Goku, help me!
Run!
What's that?
[ROCK MONSTER growling]
[GOKU]
Giant rock guy!
[ROCK MONSTER growls]
This is getting us nowhere.
No more games.
So long!
[ROCK MONSTER roars]
This fight's... over!
[yells]
[ROCK MONSTER roars]
[CHICHI sighs]
Let's go.
Okay!
[BOTH gasp]
[sputtering]
[gasping]
[BOTH]
Ah!
[BOTH panting]
[groans]
Goku, your leg!
We can't stop now!
[BOTH panting]
[CHICHI screams]
ChiChi.
[CHICHI chuckles]
Lucky girl, I guess.
[giggles]
[DEMONS laugh]
[CHICHI]
Goku, over there!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[BEAST growls]
[CHICHI]
We can't fight it. Let's go!
[BEAST roaring]
[GOKU] I couldn't have healed
so quickly. This isn't real.
[BEAST roars]
Don't worry.
[CHICHI]
Are we seeing the same creature?
This is the perfect
time to worry!
It's all an illusion!
Does he know?
[GOKU]
Please! Trust me!
You're right!
Hold onto me, ChiChi.
We're going for a ride.
Okay!
[BEAST roars]
[GOKU grunts]
[CHICHI gasps]
[WOMAN]
Incredible!
They're the first humans
to ever cross over alive!
[groans]
[CHICHI]
Did we make it? Where are we?
[GOKU]
It's just as I thought.
Everything we saw
was all in our minds.
[CHICHI] I never knew I had
such a vivid imagination.
[GOKU]
All of it, fake.
We were never in any danger.
But I"ll bet this
entrance is real.
[OX KING grunting, yelling]
[OX KING]
Not again!
There's nowhere left to run.
I guess...we found it!
This must be the furnace.
It's gigantic!
[GOKU]
Tajoro, come out! Tajoro!
Tajoro! Hey, can you hear me?
[MAN]
Of course I can hear you.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
Ah, Grandpa?
[CHICHI]
What?
Grandpa? Impossible! Goku?
Yes, it really is you!
It's me, your grandson!
But, how did you...
You've grown so big!
You haven't changed at all!
I should hope not.
After all, I'm dead.
What are you doing
in the Dark World?
I thought only evil was here.
[GOHAN]
Dark World? Evil?
Those are just stories
to keep away the tourists.
This place is a bridge
to the other world.
Oh, who is your
lovely companion?
My fianceé.
[GOHAN]
Fianceé?
[GOKU] Yup. This is ChiChi.
She's the Ox King's daughter.
Chi Chi, this is
my grandfather, Gohan.
Pleased to meet you.
It is an honor. This has
turned into a family reunion.
Actually, I knew you
when you were just a baby.
I was good friends with your
father. How is he doing, anyway?
Horrible! His castle's on fire!
That's why we traveled here.
We were told the Magical
Furnace could put it out.
Huh? Goku, what are
you talking about?
It's okay.
Everything will be fine.
Now that you know,
you can save his kingdom.
Whoa, hold on, son.
It's not that simple.
If the furnace is involved,
this won't be easy.
Of course it will!
You're Tajoro.
You can do anything you
want with the furnace.
Wait a minute.
You thought I was Tajoro?
No, I just work here part time.
[WOMAN]
Gohan?
Grandpa, who is that?
That, Grandson, is Tajoro.
She is the caretaker
of the magical furnace.
The name Tajoro is
actually an alias for Annin.
I've been assigned to guard her.
[ANNIN]
Gohan, are you there or not?
[GOHAN]
Yes, I'm right here.
My grandson stopped by
to pay me a visit.
[ANNIN] In that case,
I shall come to you.
[rumbling]
Gohan, my noodles,
they're soggy.
I fear there
may be a malfunction
with the Magical Furnace's
temperature regulators.
Didn't you replace
them last week?
Huh?
I don't think there's anything--
[GOKU]
So, you're Tajoro!
My name is Goku, and I have
a favor to ask of you.
Please put out the Magical Fire!
[gasps]
I beg of you, please help us.
My father is trapped
within the flames.
Unless I'm mistaken,
the Ox King's castle
is located on the
other side of this mountain.
That would put it in
the fire's direct path.
Perhaps there's a hole
in the furnace.
Then you'll have to find a
way to turn off the furnace.
I'm afraid I can't
do that, Goku.
[GOKU]
What do you mean? Why not?
[ANNIN] In theory, if the
magical fire were extinguished,
the plains of existence would
be thrown into utter chaos.
Actually, that sounds
like alot of fun.
Utter chaos? Annin, what
are you saying?
Annin, please!
You must help.
Grandpa!
[grunting]
Mh-hm... mh-hm.
I'm sorry, but the magical
flame cannot be put out,
for you or anyone.
Now, you wouldn't want
to be responsible
for the world's
greatest disaster.
Hm?
[slurps]
[NARRATOR]
What is the mysterious disaster
Annin speaks of?
How will Goku solve
the impossible dilemma?
Will he risk the fate of the
world to save ChiChi's father?
Don't miss the
extraordinary conclusion
on the final episode
of Dragon Ball.