[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Having found 5 Dragon Balls,
Master Roshi and the others
attempted to lure
King Piccolo into a trap
to gain the remaining two.
[PICCOLO] I guess I should
keep these in a safe place.
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately, those
plans went down the drain
when Piccolo
swallowed the orbs.
The only option for us now
is to knock him over
and pump those balls
out of his rotten hide!
I must fight him, Master!
I must!
[ROSHI]
No, Tien, you stay out of this!
It's the only way!
[NARRATOR] Fearing for
his students' safety,
Master Roshi decided
to alter his plan
and leave his
students out of it.
Tell Goku I was proud.
Chiaotzu, stay hidden!
Do not come out until it's over,
no matter what happens!
[CHIAOTZU]
Yes, Master, okay!
[NARRATOR]
With his team secured,
Master Roshi challenged
King Piccolo to a duel.
The battle to save
the planet was at hand
and the fate of all mankind
rested on the
Turtle Hermit's shoulders.
[OOLONG]
It's true! I know it!
[OOLONG] See?
We've got seven Dragon Balls!
[BULMA]
No, Oolong. There's only five.
I know, but somehow
two of them just disappeared.
[PUAR] Disappeared?
Yes, vanished.
[YAMCHA laughs]
No way.
It's the truth!
[BULMA] I don't see how
that could have happened.
I mean, short of
them being ingested,
there's no way they
wouldn't show up on my radar.
It's just not logical.
Wait. A moment ago,
there were seven.
That means Turtle Hermit
and King Piccolo
must be in
the same location.
This is Kame House. Come in,
Master Roshi. Please respond!
I repeat, Kame House to
Master Roshi. Please come in.
Master Roshi, are you there?
Tien Shinhan, Chiaotzu?
Is anybody there?
If you can hear me,
please say something.
Someone, answer me!
[OOLONG] With that tone,
I wouldn't answer either.
It's useless!
What could have
happened to them?
It's possible
they've been destroyed.
And it's possible you're stupid!
[YAMCHA thinking] What if
something bad has happened
to Master Roshi?
If he's defeated,
what chance do any of us stand
against those monsters?!
All of the Dragon Balls I've
collected are buried right here.
[ROSHI] You can dig them up
and take them away...
...if you can defeat me!
[chuckling]
That will be my
distinct pleasure.
I have to stay awake!
[PICCOLO] Standing before
the might of King Piccolo,
you still wish
to challenge me!
Foolish old man.
He must really have a death wish
to try and challenge
King Piccolo
out in the open like this.
Why, he doesn't even
have any support!
He could have an army
and he'd still lose.
[laughing]
Imbecile.
[PICCOLO] Obviously you have
no idea who I am.
Otherwise, you'd understand
that this path you have chosen
is suicidal.
This isn't the first
time we've met, monster!
[laughing]
Then you must realize that I
will soon send you to oblivion!
[ROSHI] Yeah, yeah.
I've heard that before.
The only one who's gonna
take a dirt nap here is you,
unless you decide
to play it smart
and give me
your Dragon Balls!
[PICCOLO]
If that was a joke,
then I'm still waiting
for the punch line.
Your humor is wearing thin.
[PICCOLO]
You want my Dragon Balls?
Then here.
They're all yours, old man.
Take them if you can.
[PICCOLO]
Come on. Here's your chance.
What are you waiting for?
Take it!
What's the matter?
Are you too scared? Here.
So be it. You see, you have
succumbed to your fear, old man.
Don't feel bad.
I have that effect on people.
So?
[ROSHI chuckles]
[PICCOLO] You're really serious,
aren't you?
Then by all means...
[PICCOLO] Die.
[yells]
[PICCOLO laughing]
He lasted longer
than I expected.
[PICCOLO] Well, well. Look who
wants another dose of pain.
Good, good.
I have a lot to dish out.
Now tell me, old man,
before you die,
how does it feel
to be nothing?!
Fool!
Why do you stand in my way?!
[ROSHI]
Because you are in mine.
How so?
With you threatening the world,
how am I supposed to
enjoy my exercise programs?
Huh?
You human!
Get up! Get on your feet!
A quick death
is too good for you!
I'm going to make you
suffer beyond imagination!
So you think you're a warrior.
Then, impress me.
What's he doing?
He's not nearly
as strong as he boasts.
[PICCOLO] Fight me, warrior!
Show me the power!
Then allow me!
[screams]
[PICCOLO thinking]
Stupid old man.
What does he hope to gain
by this passive resistance?
This is folly!
I have no interest
in fighting you.
You're right.
I'm no match for you.
You possess powers
far greater than my own.
But for every obstacle
there is a solution.
I can still defeat you.
No!
Master, don't do it!
You mustn't!
[PICCOLO]
What are you blabbering about?!
[ROSHI] You know what I'm
talking about all too well.
I told you this wasn't
the first time we'd met.
Many years ago,
I faced you in battle.
I was there the day
my Master stared you down.
The day you blinked.
Go on.
Do you want to know
my Master's name?
It's Mutaito.
Not again!
[PICCOLO yelling]
Boy, I hope that tower you're
talking about shows up soon.
Korin's Tower... We're close.
[YAJIROBE]
You're sweating buckets!
There's more water in here
than there is outside.
I must get there very soon.
Don't you worry.
I just hope they have
a good doctor who's in.
Korin can help me.
I see. So Korin is
the name of your doctor?
He's a cat.
He must be worse off
than I thought.
[PICCOLO] Y-You mean--
[ROSHI] Here you go.
This should jog your memory.
[PICCOLO]
Th-The Electronic Jar!
[ROSHI] Home, sweet home.
Not the jar!
[MUTAITO, PICCOLO yelling]
[MUTAITO] Close it!
I-I can't believe it!
Impossible!
[TIEN]
The Evil Containment Wave!
Master Roshi, you can't!
If you use it, you'll die!
[groaning]
You remember that special day!
The day you were sealed
in the Electronic Jar
by Master Mutaito.
And I'm sure you also remember
the special technique
that put you there!
[PILAF] That's strange.
Why is King Piccolo shaking?
Is he cold?
It's not windy.
Oh, poor Majesty!
He's frightened! Piccolo!
What's going on?!
Evil Containment!
[yelling]
M-Master!
[TIEN thinking]
It's just as Master described!
I-I missed it!
[PICCOLO panting]
Stupid! That was like
an amateur. I...I failed.
[ALL sigh]
You haven't won. Your dark
dreams will never come true.
Somehow, someone will
succeed where I failed.
Until that day, live in fear.
You will fall.
We're only human,
but we will survive.
[TIEN thinking]
Don't give up, Master!
[CHIAOTZU thinking]
Master Roshi!
We will survive.
[gasps]
What's the matter? Are you
hurting? What's going on?
Something is wrong, very wrong.
You're acting pretty strange.
I guess maybe I kept you under
the water a little bit too long.
[chuckling]
[laughing]
Yes, he's dead! The fool's dead!
--He did it!
--Incredible!
[PICCOLO] That was too close!
I never expected he would know
about the Evil Containment Wave.
The old man was sly,
but now he's gone forever.
I'm free! Truly free!
No one on this pathetic planet
will harm me ever again!
[laughing]
It's time.
The seven Dragon Balls are mine!
At last I will reclaim my youth
and with it
all my glorious power!
[TIEN thinking]
Youth?! That's what he's after.
He'll be unstoppable!
Now Dragon, appear before me!
[CHIAOTZU thinking] Those dark
clouds! Something is coming!
Look at that! It's getting
kinda dark for being mid-day.
Nightfall sure comes early
in this neck of the woods.
Wait a minute. Three years ago,
the same thing happened!
The Eternal Dragon
will soon appear.
Shu, please tell me
you brought my camera.
I have to take pictures!
[TIEN thinking]
This can't be happening!
If that monster
gets his youth back,
nobody will be able
to control him.
It'll be the end of the world!
[PILAF] Where's my camera?!
[yelling]
Look!
The Eternal Dragon!
[roars]
Magnificent!
[NARRATOR] Despite the
Turtle Hermit's best efforts,
King Piccolo prevailed to
call forth the Eternal Dragon.
With his youth but a wish away,
can anyone stop
the majestic monster
from conquering the world?
Tune in next time as
the adventure continues
on Dragon Ball!