[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Fearing Goku would attack
the Red Ribbon Army
by himself, Bulma dispatched
a probe to search
for her friend and
any sign of trouble.
Determining her
suspicion was valid;
she assembled Yamcha and
the others to assist Goku
in his risky assault.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Commander Red anxiously
awaited the return of Mercenary
Tao and the Dragon Balls
he was to have stolen from Goku.
However, it was Goku,
not the hired assassin,
who prevailed and was now on his
way to face the maniacal tyrant.
[NARRATOR] No matter the cost,
Goku was determined
to retrieve the Dragon Balls
in Commander Red's possession.
For only with all seven
balls could he summon
the Eternal Dragon and
restore life to Upa's father.
[NARRATOR] And so,
Goku and his friends
have embarked on their most
perilous adventure yet.
One that will lead
them to war against
the entire Red Ribbon empire.
[NARRATOR] It's time!
The final showdown has begun!
[YAMCHA]
So far, so good.
The navigational radar is clear
and all systems check out.
[YAMCHA] We've now reached
cruising altitude.
[OOLONG] This trip is as far
from a cruise as you can get!
I don't know why we even
bothered to bring him.
All he does is
think about himself!
Why risk my life?
Give me one good reason.
You're going; it's not
up for discussion!
Anyway, I can
remember a time or two
when Goku helped
you out of a jam!
[TURTLE]
Uh, Excuse me, Yamcha?
Do you think there's
anything that an old turtle
like me can do to help?
[LAUNCH] I think we could
put ya to good use!
Yes sir, turtle soup will
make a nice victory meal!
--[ALL scream]
--No, Launch, No!
That girl is nuts!
Hey, Master Roshi?
Yeah, son?
Do you have any idea
where Krillin ran off to?
He went for a swim
across the sea,
and some shopping
on the mainland.
He was too impatient to wait
until he could get a ride.
We could sure use his help, too.
Do you think we could
still catch up to him?
[ROSHI]
We oughtta be able to spot him
--if we fly a little lower-- Ah!
--[YAMCHA] Cool. Now, everyone
keep your eyes peeled!
Please tell me you remembered to
disarm all the defense systems.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Of course!
Checked and
double-checked, Commander!
[RED]
Good.
A shower of missiles wouldn't
make a very good welcome
for Mercenary Tao.
No sir!
[RED chuckles]
Four more Dragon Balls...
Did you make the arrangements
for the banquet in Tao's honor?
Yes. It's all done.
[beeping]
[SIGNALMAN]
Unit 84, unit 8-4.
Locate Mercenary Tao and escort
him to the main building.
Roger that!
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN]
I've been out here forever...
[KRILLIN yelps]
[KRILLIN panting]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN screams]
Huh?
Krillin!
Did we scare you?
[KRILLIN] Nah, I was
just messin' with ya.
What's up?
You have great timing.
I was hoping for a ride home!
[BULMA]
Well, get in, quick!
[KRILLIN]
Uh, okay... Hey!
What happened to my clothes?
Krillin! Get in the plane!
[KRILLIN] Would it have killed
you to go back for my stuff?
Ugh! Watch it! If my hair
frizzes, you're in trouble!
Oh! Sorry, Bulma.
Did I hear you say
Goku's on his way
to the Red Ribbon
compound by himself?!
Yep, that's right.
What in the world
was he thinking?!
He's obviously not thinking!
[OOLONG]
You can say that again!
Heh, heh! This'll be fun!
[KRILLIN]
You know Launch,
everyone else
sees this as work...
But I get the feeling
you're actually
looking forward to it,
like a vacation.
Hey Bulma!
Am I going the right
direction here? Look!
[BULMA]
Hm...
[BULMA] You're on track.
Just fly straight.
How much time do we have
before we need to land?
Oh. I'd say about half an hour.
How's the fuel?
We'll have enough.
[OOLONG chuckles] Well, you two
make quite a team, don't ya?
When's the wedding?
[BOTH gasp]
Hey! Knock it off, Oolong!
[PUAR, OOLONG gasp]
Hmph. Yamcha?
Huh?
Don't think this
means that I'm not
mad at you anymore.
But this is an emergency, so we
can bury the hatchet for now.
But just for now!
Uh...
[TURTLE, PUAR]
Aw...
Uh... Okay, Bulma.
We'll talk everything out later
when we have plenty of time!
[OOLONG]
If we make it to 'later'.
[SIGNALMAN]
Huh? Sir!
He's arrived!
Good.
[SIGNALMAN]
Unit Number 84!
Come in! Come in 84! Do you have
a visual of Mercenary Tao yet?
[PILOT]
Yes, I see someone coming!
Huh?
Now to get those Dragon Balls!
Hey! It's not Tao!
It's some kid on a cloud!
[GOKU yells]
Oh, no!
[GOKU growls, laughs]
[GOKU grunting]
Power pole extend!
Go!
[GOKU yells]
[PILOT screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[SIGNALMAN]
I'm losing you, 84!
Can you hear me, soldier?
Unit 84, what's happening?
[RED]
What now?
The helicopter may have
been intercepted, sir!
What?! How can that be?!
[BEAR screams] Men! Switch the
views on the radar! Sir!
[RED]
What've you got?
[BEAR]
It's him!
[RED screams] No! How did
that punk kid get in here?
[STAFF OFFICER] The boy must
have defeated Mercenary Tao!
How can that be possible?
Get that security system
up and running again,
and call all available men
to their posts immediately!
[BEAR]
Yes, Commander!
[SIGNALMAN] Get the defense
shield up right now!
[RED growls] You little brat!
I'll get you this time!
[GOKU grunting]
The calculations
have been completed.
Battle units! Stay alert
and await further orders!
[UNIT SOLDIER] Roger!
[RED] Do it now!
[BEAR]
We're all set up, sir!
Then its all systems go
for a little pest control!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU yelping]
That was close!
[GOKU yelps] Nimbus cloud!
We have to go faster!
Oh!
[GOKU yelps]
Uh-oh!
[GOKU]
Ha ha!
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU gasps]
Hm...
[GOKU yelling]
He's here!
[GOKU yells]
He's fast!
Hey! Here I come!
You blasted morons!
You're all about as useful
as snowshoes in summer!
Listen! Keep him
outside no matter what!
I'm afraid it's too late
for that, commander!
[RED gasps]
He's already in sector 12!
[RED growls]
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention all personnel!
Intruder Alert!
Base breached in Sector 12!
Do not let him through!
Destroy the trespasser on sight!
That's a direct order
from Commander Red!
All men to
sector 12 immediately!
[SOLIERS growl]
[SOLDIERS groaning,
GOKU grunting]
[GOKU grunting]
[SOLDIER 4 groans]
[GOKU yells]
[SOLDIERS grunt]
[GOKU]
That way!
I wonder where everyone went?
No one seems to be here!
[GOKU yelps,
SOLDIERS cackling]
[SOLDIER]
Ready boys? Fire!
[GOKU yelping]
[SOLDIER 6]
We've been expecting you!
You missed me.
[SOLDIER 6 screaming,
GOKU growling
[SOLDIER 6 groans]
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[SOLDIER 7 screams,
SOLDIER DOG 1 groans]
[VIOLET]
Hm...
Where is it?
How much further till
we reach their base?
Don't worry, we'll see
it soon enough.
[OOLONG]
We must have missed it.
Let's go back to
where we started!
No, we didn't pass
it up; it's too big!
Take a hint! Let's go home!
--[OOLONG screams]
--[YAMCHA] Huh?
[BULMA]
A-ha! See that snowy mountain?
The headquarters is
on the other side.
I'm sure of it!
Okay!
Hey, Bulma?
Look out the back and see
if anyone is following us.
Uh... I don't see anything
out there but snow.
You sure?
Oh, no... I think
I see something!
What is that Bulma?
[BULMA]
It's a shark!
[KRILLIN]
Did you say shark?
[PUAR]
Sharks don't live in snow!
[PUAR, OOLONG, BULMA]
It's a missile!
What?!
Now?
[KRILLIN]
It's right on our tail!
[BULMA] I've seen this before.
It's a chaser missile!
They're programmed
to never give up.
Now that's persistence!
See, I told you we
should've gone home!
Mommy!
Rats!
Oh! I bet that's it...
That's how it works...
What do you mean?
Okay, I think it's activated
by a heat source.
So, what do we do?
Get rid of the booster jet.
See, it only chases
the source of the heat.
It's a bit unsophisticated
by modern day standards.
Well, it still almost got us!
That's some quick
thinkin' there!
Now, how about
some quick kissin'?
You will never touch these lips!
[ALL laughing]
Colonel Violet! Come quick!
Some kid is taking over!
Colonel Violet? What're you--
[VIOLET] No time, my boy.
I have a previous engagement.
I'm sure you men
can handle it.
See ya!
[GOKU grunting]
[SOLDIER 8]
Hey!
[SOLDIER 8 groans]
Ka, Me, Ha...
[GOKU]
Me...
Ha!
[RED]
What's happening?!
You guys, he's over here!
[SOLDIERS growling]
[GOKU grunting,
SOLDIERS groaning]
Sir! He seems to be headed
straight for Wing Number Eight!
[RED] Just as I suspected!
He's after the Dragon Balls!
Commander, you should evacuate
to a secure location.
I'll do no such thing!
I refuse to hide away from
some little squirt of a kid!
But he was strong
enough to beat Tao,
and now our soldiers
are running in terror!
He's still no match
for the Red Ribbon Army!
[RED growling]
[GOKU] There! The Dragon Balls
must be in that building!
[GOKU grunts]
Hey, you'd better watch where
you point that thing! It hurts!
[SOLDIER 9] Huh? Is this
kid some kind of robot?
[BEAR]
He's made it to Wing Eight,
and we've lost half of
our men already, sir!
And I don't care!
Maybe you don't believe
this army is unstoppable,
but I'd bet my life
on it! Hurry up!
We're going to the Eighth Wing!
[RED panting]
Ah! I will never let him
take you two away from me.
That boy will never beat me!
[STAFF OFFICER]
Commander Red, please.
The odds are against us. The
kid is incredibly strong, sir.
The complex is in total chaos.
Besides, he already put our
best officers out of commission
before he even came here.
Are the Dragon Balls really
worth all this trouble?
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunting,
SOLDIERS groaning]
[GOKU]
Oh! I have to go higher I guess.
But where are the stairs?
[GOKU]
Oh well.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[GOKU laughs]
[RED growls]
Fool! He doesn't even
know how to work an elevator.
Somebody explain to me how
the world's strongest army
could lose to this imbecile?!
[NARRATOR]
Goku is closing in on his goal
of confiscating the Dragon Balls
from Commander Red.
So far, the Red Ribbon
forces have been
unable to withstand
our hero's assault.
But for how long can Goku
sustain his offensive against
these overwhelming odds?
Hopefully, long enough for
Yamcha and the rest of the gang
to come to his aid!
Because if Commander Red
has his way,
then Goku is about to be
stopped in his tracks!
[NARRATOR]
You won't want to miss round two
of this important battle,
next time on Dragon Ball!