[NARRATOR] Shrouded in
the dark and fog of night,
strange and frightening things
may lurk about...
Unexpected evil could be
just around the corner...
And sometimes, the line between
nightmare and reality
can shift in an instant...
[GIRL gasps]
[clock chimes]
[squelching,
GIRL gasps]
[wet splatters]
[GIRL gasps]
[screams]
[whimpers]
[GIRL shrieks]
[GOKU growls]
[NARRATOR] Life can be
a drag when you're
the strongest kid around
looking for a challenge!
But Goku will try anything to
make himself stronger
for the next Tournament!
One thing is certain: our hero
won't have long to wait
before a
new adventure finds him
on his journey around the world!
[OLD WOMAN]
What are you doing, young man?
Oh, this? I'm training myself!
Ahhh...
Well, you'd better find
someplace else to do it.
It's not safe here.
What do you mean?
Look... do you see
that castle down there?
[GOKU] Hmm? Ohh...
Stay away from it...
It's surrounded
by a town of demons!
[GOKU] Demons? Like ghosts?
Yes!
And at the castle
this very morning,
they found that the princess
was missing from her room!
The fiends must have
snatched her away
in the middle of the night!
Everyone thinks the
demons snuck through
the Portal of the Dead
to get her!
[GOKU] The Portal of the Dead?
What's that?
[OLD WOMAN] It's the doorway
between our world
and the demon world.
[GOKU] Oh, I see.
You should get out of here
right away, little boy.
For your own good!
[stomach growls]
[GOKU groans]
[laughs]
Wait. I can quiet that tummy.
They're just leftovers,
but you're welcome to them!
[GOKU] Thank you, lady!
Bye now!
[GOKU] Bye!
Looks pretty normal to me.
Hm...
Huh?
There's an upside-down
demon outside!
--Oh!
--Take a look!
[GOKU] What was that?
You'd better get
your eyes checked out.
It's just a little boy!
[whimpers]
[grunts]
Wait! No kid is that strong!
He's got to be some kind
of supernatural being!
[gasps]
[whimpering]
Anybody there?
[MAN B] He's so fast!
[MAN C] Unnaturally so!
[MAN D] He must be an
evil spirit!
That really wasn't very nice!
I only came here
to try and help you!
Come out now!
[OLD MAN] Wait!
Hang on a minute!
Stop... Let's talk about this.
[whimpering]
[wolf howls]
Are you sure that this
boy is capable
of rescuing Princess Meesa
from Demon Land?
[OLD MAN] He may not
look like much,
but he seems to be highly
trained and incredibly strong.
You should have seen him
lift that boulder
like it was only a pebble!
Oh, and there was the tree, too.
I think he may be
our best hope, your majesty.
I believe what you tell me,
but as strong as he is,
he still may be no
match for Shula.
He's the best fighter
in all of Demon Land!
If I may say so,
it's worth a shot, sir.
The kid said he was willing
to take on any opponent,
and the tougher, the better!
Well, I suppose
we don't have a choice.
Yum! That was so good!
You have a great cook!
I'm totally stuffed!
[KING] Well, boy,
what do they call you?
Are you talking to me?
My name is Goku.
Hey, there, mind your manners
now! You're talking to the king!
[KING] Goku?
Yes, King?
You realize that you may
not be able to come back
once you've gone through the
Portal of the Dead, don't you?
Why wouldn't I be able
to come back?
[KING] Once the demons find out
that you have come
from the living world,
they won't rest
until they've captured you.
Then they will keep you as their
prisoner in Demon Land
for the rest of your life.
Then I just won't let
myself get caught!
[KING laughs]
That's a laugh!
[GOKU laughs]
Why are we laughing?
[growls]
Because you're so
terribly naïve!
Of course you'll be caught!
There are thousands
of demons there!
It will be impossible
to escape them all!
This boy is just playing around.
Get him out of my sight!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Let go of me!
[KNIGHTS grunt]
Why'd you do that?
I haven't done anything wrong!
[KING] Huh?!
[whimpering]
[KNIGHTS yell]
[gasps]
[GOKU yells,
KNIGHTS grunt]
If you have a problem,
you could try talking to
me about it, you know?!
I really must apologize.
I misjudged you. Forgive me.
Sure!
[sighing]
I've never heard of a child
being such a great fighter,
but now I've seen it
with my own eyes.
Who was your teacher?
Oh, he's called
Master Roshi.
Roshi? You mean
the Turtle Hermit?
He's legendary among
the martial arts masters.
isn't he?
[QUEEN] Mm-hmm!
Still... As I mentioned to you
earlier, the demon called Shula
is the most fearsome warrior
in the entire underworld.
Many brave men
have faced him and lost.
Each paid a high price
for their failure.
They were never to be seen
in this world again.
I'll get your daughter,
and I'll come back!
I hope so.
[yelling,
KING gasps]
[yelling continues]
What is that?
Shula has jammed the Portal of
the Dead with his sword.
Now the gate is stuck open
and the fiends have been able
to come and go as they please.
The villagers are terrified!
[horn sounds,
yelling]
They always come and
steal our harvest.
We barely have enough
to feed ourselves!
Okay! I'll go get it back!
Wait a minute!
This mission is too important
to run off unprepared.
If you're going to rescue Meesa,
you have to wait
until the time is just right.
Why can't I go now?
You must have patience.
There is a time for all things.
Beating the demons is possible
if you go about it wisely.
I'll wait if you want me to.
Oh, so that's where the
Demons come from,
the Pot Hole of the Dead.
No, the Portal of the Dead,
it means the "doorway"!
Now, do you see the way Shula's
sword props the gate wide open?
That's why the spirits are able
to roam freely in our world.
[GOKU] I see...
So why don't you
just pull it out?
[KING] No one has ever been
able to budge the blade,
not even an inch.
For the sword to loosen, Shula
must first be defeated.
If we can't remove it, the door
will stay open forever.
And our village will remain
doomed to be tormented
by these fiends
for all of eternity.
That guy is really
tough to beat, I guess?
From what I've been told, he has
never lost a fight to anyone.
Okay! I'll just pull
this out first!
[grunts]
Stop that. You'll just
wear yourself out.
It will only move
when Shula has been defeated.
[grunts]
Whew! It didn't
wiggle one bit!
[KING] To beat Shula's curse,
you must beat him.
It's the only way.
I'll fight him then.
He can't be as tough
as they say.
[KING] Hmm.
Good! I've been wanting
to test myself.
This should be fun!
Be careful in there, Goku!
See ya!
Hey! What's taking
so long with that grub?
Whoa! Keep your pants on!
What's that supposed to be?
You serving me garbage?!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[LAUNCH]
What are you laughing at?!
[gasps]
[ROSHI] Ehh... Ah...
Oh, well, uh!
Something in the air
is tickling my nose!
[LAUNCH] I couldn't care less!
Now get lost
until I need you again!
[ROSHI squeals]
Yes, Launch...
[NARRATOR]
While Goku is off on his own,
Krillin and Yamcha are
hard at work preparing
for the World Martial
Arts Tournament
under the direction of
their mentor, Master Roshi.
His exercises are
as grueling as ever,
and the pupils are
quickly learning
to think on their feet!
I hope Goku's training
is less dangerous than ours!
If I know him,
he's probably getting himself
into some kind of trouble...
I'll bet you're right!
Who did that?!
Who goes there?
I'm going over there!
Wait! You need permission!
What's a "permission"?
You need a special pass
from the Ruler of the Underworld
to go through here!
But I've never met him!
Then go back
where you came from,
while you still have your life!
[growls] So foolish!
[growls] Let go!
[GOKU grunts]
[growling]
[grunts]
You're mine, kid!
[yells]
[WOMAN] Hold it!
[BOTH] Huh?
You must be quite a
special little boy
to push around great big Gola.
He's no weakling, you know?
I must say,
I'm pleasantly surprised!
What's your name, sport?
It's Goku. What's your name?
Melee.
I'm the girl to know if you
want to get past this point.
[GOKU] So then maybe you can let
me through so I can find Shula.
Huh?
Hey!
Wait a minute!
Have you lost your mind?
You're not really on
your way to see Shula, are you?
Yes, I'm gonna
fight him and beat him,
and then I'm gonna take Princess
Meesa back to her family!
[GOLA laughs]
Do you have any idea
how dangerous he is?
[GOKU] I'm not afraid of him!
Now where is he?
Are you absolutely sure
about this, kid?
I told the king I'd help.
I always keep my promises,
no matter how tough!
Honestly, Goku, he could
tear you limb from limb.
[GOLA] Besides, Shula's marrying
Princess Meesa tonight.
He's probably too busy
to see you now.
They're getting married?
Yeah, he's planning a big party
for all the underworld!
Then I'd better hurry!
Show me where
to find him right now!
[MELEE] Okay!
I'll take you to see him.
Just follow me,
and don't fall behind!
No, Melee!
[MELEE giggles]
[DEMONS chattering, laughing]
[DEMONS laugh]
Don't be bashful, my darling.
You don't want to miss tonight's
special entertainment, do you?
[M.C.] Ghouls and boys,
in honor of the impending
nuptials, how about a fight?
Any brave soul want to put
their skills to the test?
[GOKU] I'll do it!
[DEMONS cheer]
Where did that boy come from?
This reeks of
Melee's handiwork.
Agreed.
But it must be a joke.
That kid's a creampuff!
I'd say that sounds
like a fair assessment.
[GOKU] Oh, but don't come down
unless you're really
strong, please!
How arrogant!
Go down there and
make sure he loses.
Okay!
[chuckles]
[GOKU] Is he my opponent?
[M.C.] That's right. You want
to back out now, little one?
[GOKU] No!
I can beat this guy!
Then I guess I won't
take it easy on you after all!
Let's go!
[WART MAN growls]
[GOKU yells]
[WART MAN groans]
Oh!
[SHULA growls]
Shula won't let him
get away with that!
Now it's getting
interesting!
[M.C.] Anyone else want to
challenge this boy?
No way. I want Shula
to be my opponent this time!
[M.C.] Take that back!
You don't know
what you're saying!
[DEMONS yelling]
[SHULA] You must be
brave or stupid!
I'm not either of those guys.
I'm Goku!
In that case,
I'll fight you, as you wish.
So you're Shula?
[SHULA] At your service!
Okay! You must be Meesa!
Uh-huh.
I'm gonna save you!
[SHULA grunts]
[GOKU] Whoa!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU]
Hey! I wasn't ready!
[SHULA]
You're complaining already?
I'm just getting started!
[GOKU] Then let's go!
[grunts]
[growls]
[yells]
--[SHULA] Hmph.
--[MEESA groans]
Amazing!
Yes!
You're really good! Very tough!
What the...?
But now it's my turn!
Ka-me...
Ha-me...
[GOKU] HA!
[grunts]
[GOKU growls,
SHULA gasps]
[blows landing,
SHULA grunts]
Now, Goku!
Come on! Let's get outta here!
[DEMONS yelling]
You must be really
strong to defeat Shula!
Nah, he's just been in
this dark place too long!
He can't handle bright light!
I think I just got pretty lucky!
[MELEE] Goku!
Don't forget to pull out the
sword when you get outside!
Okay!
Take care, boy!
[GOKU] Thanks,
but why did you help me?
Aren't you going to
get in trouble?
It's good to shake things up
around here once in a while.
It will blow over soon.
[MELEE] Go on!
I'll take care of them!
Thanks! Good luck!
Yeah, thanks for everything!
I'll see you again sometime.
But not anytime soon, though.
[HORSE whinnies]
Look! It's Meesa!
Oh!
Oh! Mom!
[DEMONS yelling growing louder]
Right! The sword!
[MELEE]
You know the rules!
You cannot go through
here without a pass!
But Shula sent us
to get the kid!
If he wanted you
to go outside,
he would have sent you
with a permission slip!
A rule is a rule!
[SHULA] I knew the two of you
were in on this!
Oh, no! Shula!
It's okay! Head out!
[DEMONS yelling]
[GOKU grunts]
[DEOMONS yelling]
[GOKU grunts, yells]
It's out!
[MELEE] Now only those with a
key can enter the living world!
The way it should
have been all along!
[SHULA] That little
kid... he did me in!
This must be yours.
Heads up!
Thanks...
It's good for the soul to taste
defeat sometimes, you know?
I guess.
Well, there's no use in letting
a good party go to waste.
You want to come?
--[GOLA chuckles]
--[MELEE] Why not?
Too bad about the wedding.
[SHULA laughs]
[MELEE laughs]
[GOLA laughs]
♪ [GUARD A] For he's
a jolly good fellow! ♪
[NARRATOR] It's another
happy ending, thanks to Goku!
The demons are back
where they belong
and this peaceful village
can finally return to normal!
But this joyous celebration is
just a brief break for our hero.
He's got to get on with his
training
if he hopes to win
the next tournament!