(snip)
(CHITO sleeping) (snip snip)
(snip snip)
(snipping continues)
(sigh)
Alright.
[MAKOTO]
Chito.
(sleepy mew)
Mrow...
Do you mind getting
up for a wee bit?
(meow?)
Every now and again, I
would like to air out that
cushion you're sitting on.
(stretching mew)
I appreciate you doing that.
[MAKOTO]
Ah! This is...
♪Opening Song♪
Well this...
(CHITO meowing)
Huh?
(talking meows)
You're probably right. It's
definitely too small for me.
It's also tight on my arms.
Meowowow...
Yeah that's a good point.
I made it back when I
entered middle school
for the first time,
so I was bound to
grow out of it.
Ah, looks like the
moths nibbled‐ Uh!
Hold on! That's not it! It's
shredded all over the place!
Chito? Did you do this?
(huff meow)
(talking meows)
Well that's quite alright. Plus
it's too small for me anyway.
(fabric ripping)
Huh?
There goes that one.
I guess I need to
make a new one...
(CHITO meowing)
[NANA]
Then you keep going straight
past this point,
walk a few more steps and
turn right, you'll see a
drug store...
[NANA]
The fabric store is across
the street from there.
It's quite far. You
sure you'll be okay?
I‐I'll be fine... probably.
I think I can make it there.
Are you sure about that? It's
no bother driving you there.
No, it's okay. I'm up
for the challenge.
Huh?
One of my life goals
is improving my bad
sense of direction.
Oh, that's
the spirit!
Besides, I'll have Chito
with me. I'll be fine.
(prideful meow)
(laughter)
Okay got it. Anyhow...
this robe is really
something.
You made it all by yourself?
It's really made quite well.
Thank you. Making robes
myself means I can design
them how I want.
Plus it's a lot cheaper too.
That's reasonable.
Does Akane make her own?
Ah... she told me she
would rather buy all
of her robes online.
[NANA]
(laughing) I see.
Oh, my. This is
all ripped up.
(busted meow)
(guilty faded meow)
Chito made a
big mess of it.
Now you can't
be doing that.
Okay. I'm heading out.
Take care out
there! Hmh!
Oh?
[NANA] Makoto, wait! The map!
[MAKOTO] Oh?
(confusion)
Hmm? Huh? Hmm?
(annoyed)
Is this the direction
I need to head?
(affirmative meow)
Mm.
Hop on.
Mrow!
♪♪
(settling mews)
(intrigued meow)
(talking meows)
[MAKOTO] Huh?
(laughing)
I know, Chito, it's fun since
it doesn't hurt to ride.
(agreement meow)
All my training
has paid off.
(distant drumming)
(intrigued meow)(long meow)
Huh?
[MAKOTO]
Ah, of course. It's almost time
for the Neputa Festival.
[AKANE]
Cheers!
[MAKOTO] Eh?
[MEN] Cheers to that!
(ALL laughing happily)
(AKANE chugging)
[MAKOTO] Uh...
[CHITO] (judging mew)
[MAKOTO]
Um... okay. From here I'm
pretty sure this is the
right direction...
(CHITO meows)
Oh!
(talking meows)
Looks like she's reading
fortunes right now.
Mrow.
Yeah, you're right.
She seems to be getting
a lot of customers.
Oh?
(small giggle)
Here.
Huh?
Oh...
(Crossroad dinging)
(Train approaching)
(dinging stops)
[MAKOTO]
Uh... it should...
be somewhere around here...
Hmmm...
I guess I need
to ask someone.
[NAO]
Oh?
Well, well, well.
That girl with the cat
sure looks familiar.
[NAO]
Makoto!
Huh?
Hey there, Nao.
How're ya doing?
Out on a delivery?
Mhmm. I've been running
around all over town.
Sounds like hard work.
Well I've gotta earn my
allowance wherever I can.
I'm thankful for the work.
(giggling)
Ah, that's right.
Makoto, do you have
plans tomorrow?
Not yet. Why
are you asking?
Because. Wanna go to
the festival with me?
Yes. Cool. That
sounds good.
Excellent. I'll get
in touch with you later.
Okay... please ride safely.
[CHITO]
Mraw! (talking meows)
Oh? Ah!
[MAKOTO]
Nao, wait!
(brakes squeaking)
Huh?
What's up?
Sorry about that.
I'm trying to find out
where this store is...
Oh?
Uh...
[NAO]
Looks like it's over there.
[MAKOTO]
Ah! Here it is.
See... we finally made it
Chito! We didn't even get
lost on our way here.
(grumbling meow)
(Door chime ringing)
Hmm...
Oh... Ah!
[MAKOTO]
Wow! This color is perfect.
This seems like sturdy
and durable fabric.
I think I'll use it
for the outer layer.
Hey, what do you
think of it, Chito?
(not impressed mew)
Mweooow!
Huh? You found
something even better?
Reow!
Ummm...
[MAKOTO]
Chito, I think this might
be a bit too flashy.
Robes are generally
supposed to look plain.
This would really stand out
when I'm flying during the day.
(grumbling mew)
[MAKOTO] Hm?
[MAKOTO]
Check this out, Chito.
The cat's eyes
glow‐in‐the‐dark.
(excited meow)
I guess I could buy at
least a meter of this stuff.
(happy meow)
[MAKOTO]
Whoa, this store really does
offer convenient prices.
I can make another robe or
two and still stay within
my approved budget.
Hmm, what to decided?
Should I go ahead and
make one more robe?
[MAKOTO]
But one robe is all I
really need. I don't want
to get excessive here...
(meow?)
Oh?
(talking meows)
[MAKOTO]
Ah! Good idea.
That's what I'll do!
[CHINATSU]
(humming while running home)
I'm back, mom!
Hey, welcome home.
[NANA]
Remember to take your shoes
around to the front.
[CHINATSU] Okay.
(phone vibrating)
Hmh?
Hm? (laughing)
[NANA]
Chinatsu.
Hmh? What is it?
Sweetie. What's your
favorite color again?
Uh... I love red.
All right, red it is.
Huh? What is it?!
What's going on?
(laugh) A surprise.
[NANA] Something to look
forward to, sweetie.
[CHINATSU] Hm?
[CHINATSU]
No fair!
(NANA laughing)
(Door sliding closed)
Hey everyone!
Mrow, mrow, mrow.
[MAKOTO]
Chinatsu.
Hmm?
Ah, there you are.
(mumbling)
Welcome home.
Do you have a
second to spare?
Hmmm?
What are you planning to do?
What did you buy for me?
[CHINATSU]
Come on, tell me!
Hmm... it's something to
look forward to later.
Oh? That again?
Alright then, Chinatsu,
listen close. D'you know the
story of "The Grateful Crane"?
[MAKOTO]
Well this is just like that.
So until I tell you it's okay,
do not open this door.
'kay.
[MAKOTO] Oh?!
[CHITO] Mraw?!
(uneasy mews)
[MAKOTO] Wha‐What?
Chinatsu, I told
you not to open this
door, remember?
Yeah. But the old man
and old woman do open
the door... in the end.
Eh? Ah, I guess
they do.
Hey... are you gonna
make me something now?
Well, I guess it's alright.
You can go ahead and watch.
♪♪
[AL]
Ei! Eiiii! Ey!
[INUKAI]
Thank you for doing that.
I doubt any more customers
will come tonight, so
let's call it a day.
[AL] Hehehi! Heh?
[AKANE] Hey!
[INUKAI] Hmh?
(drunken) Hey.
What up. Hey there. Heyyy
[INUKAI] What's going on?
[AL] (distressed) Eiiiieie!
[AKANE] Heyyy!
[AKANE]
Heyyyy... Weee...
(drunken laughter)
[INUKAI]
Is she drunk or something?
[AKANE] (obnoxious laughter)
[INUKAI, shouting] Stop! Stop!
(crashing)
(AKANE groaning)
[INUKAI] Uhhhh...
What's with her...?
[AKANE]
(groaning) Seems I
bummped into ya.
[INUKAI] Oh...
[AKANE] Thought you were
a bit farther awayyyy.
[INUKAI]
(annoyed) I see...
(AKANE groaning)
[AKANE]
Well, it's been a while
so I thought I'd have you
read my fortune.
Sure, but
it'll cost you.
(laughing) I
got some really
good stuff
from one of the
men around here.
[AKANE]
(drunken laugh)
This will be my payment.
(uneasy)
[AL] (struggling)
[INUKAI] Uh?
(determined)
Nyiiii!
Oh little snacks! How
thoughtful of you Al!
Hm?
Alright, you can join us
if you really want to.
[AL]
Eih? Ei...
[INUKAI]
Mhm. I guess there's
no fighting it.
But just a little
for me, okay?
Oh, yay! Let's
drink to that!
Okay, I'm finished,
Chinatsu.
Wow!
It's a witch's robe.
(totally stoked)
This is amazing! Can
I really have this?
But of course. After
all, I made this robe
especially for you.
You're the best, Makoto.
You should probably say thank
you to Chito, for helping.
[MAKOTO]
She was the one who suggested
I make this robe for you.
[CHINATSU] I see!
[CHITO] (affirmative mew)
(scared meow)
(screeching mews)
(struggling meows)
[CHINATSU] Chito,
I love you so much!
(snuggling the struggling cat)
[MAKOTO] Oh?
[NANA]
Did you finish it?
Oh my. She made quite a
nice robe for you, huh,
Chinatsu?
Mhmm! (happy giggling)
(and pose!)
Oh, that was some
nice twirling.
Thanks!
You really are quite skilled
with your hands, Makoto.
[NANA]
Impressive.
Huh? Oh yeah...
[MAKOTO]
It's nothing special really...
[NANA]
Wanna take a photo?
[CHINATSU]
Yeah! Mhm!
[MAKOTO]
(giggling) You look
pretty cool, Chinatsu.
[NANA] Are you ready?
[KEI] Huh?
[CHINATSU] Okay.
[KEI] What the?
[CHINATSU] One more, one more.
[NANA] Okay...
[CHINATSU] Makoto,
you get in, too.
[MAKOTO] Sure.
[KEI] Wah!
[ALL] Huh?
[KEI] What is this?
[MAKOTO] Hey Kei, is
something the matter?
[KEI] Huh?
[KEI]
What is this thing?
Ah! How in the world
did that get over there?
That's Chito's fabric. Oh?
[KEI] Chito's fabric?
[CHINATSU] Shh.
[KEI] What were you
doing in there?
[MAKOTO] (chuckle)
[KEI]
It sounds like you all are
having a lot of fun in here.
Hey mom,
where's Chinatsu?
Hey...
Kei! Ta‐da!
Oh! Lookin'
pretty cool!
(giggling)
I know, right?
[CHINATSU]
It's time to use some magic!
[KEI] Oh?
[CHINATSU] Hey, Big brother...
turn into a big donut!
Oh no! I'm a big
round donut!
Time to dig in now, great!
(NANA &amp; MAKOTO laughing)
(stomach growling)
[CHINATSU]
I'm actually am pretty hungry.
[NANA]
Alright, let's have dinner.
(screech meows)
[CHINATSU] Sounds good.
(sleeping mews)
(sigh)
Maybe I should make it
a bit more exciting...
Perhaps something that's still
stylish while adding a dash of
cuteness,
while also keeping the witches
traditional cloaking at night
theme alive.
(door opening)
[MAKOTO] Oh?
(AKANE groaning)
(inspecting mews)
[MAKOTO] Hm?
Hey, girlll.
(drunken laugh)
Have you been
drinking again?
Huh? Since this afternoon.
First with
some old dudes.
Then later with
Inukai. (drunk sigh)
You've been drinking
since I spotted you?
[AKANE]
Ah more importantly, you
left this sitting out.
[MAKOTO]
Ah! Oh no, I forgot
to put it away.
Akane, did you see
another one with it?
Huh?
Hmm... not here.
[MAKOTO] Not here.
[CHITO] (talking meows)
I wonder if someone
came and took it.
[AKANE] Don't think so, I doubt
anyone other than witches knows
about mandrakes.
[KENNY] (soft mew)
Yeah, you're right.
[KENNY] Mraww!
[MAKOTO AKANE]
Huh?
[MAKOTO]
Ah, there it is.
Hmh?
What's wrong?
Umm...
It's uh...
Well it's twitching
around weirdly.
Hmm?
[MAKOTO] Wha..?
[AKANE] Uh...?
Could this really
be one them?
[AKANE]
Hup! I gotcha now! Come here!
[MAKOTO] Whahhh!
(laughing) I thought
we'd find one.
[KENNY]
Mraw...
Yeah...it's
a groundfish!
Groundfish?
[AKANE]
Yep. You know, fish
that live in the ground.
[AKANE]
These fish love festivals.
They come around whenever
one draws near.
So they like festivals?
That's weird.
Yep.
Eh... (bewildered)
(yelp)
Ahaha! Better watch out
there. Groundfish love
playing tricks on us.
(sigh)
Oh. Oh. Oh!
Why are there so
many of them here?
Well I had a feeling
something had to be
lurking in the background.
I should have
figured it was you.
[AKANE]
You here to see Neputa?
I see. Well, it certainly
is a fun festival.
(uncorking, giggling)
What are you
doing, Akane?
Ah... just sharing
what I have.
Huh?
(laughing) You guys are some
heavy drinkers, aren't you?
Here, have some snacks
while you're at it.
That is amazing! Do you mind
if I try and feed them, too?
Sure.
Here.
Thank you.
Hmm!
[MAKOTO] Hup!
[AKANE] Huh?
(freaking out)
(laughing)
(chasing meows)
[MAKOTO]
Akane, I feel like you've been
staying here for a while now.
I suppose you're right.
It's just so comfortable
being around here.
It is nice, isn't it?
Also... the sake
here is great, too!
Jeez, Akane...
[CHINATSU] Makoto.
[AKANE] Huh?
Hey there, Chinatsu.
Why are you up?
I had to use the bathroom.
(sleepy sigh)
(sleeping breathes)
[AKANE]
Did you make that robe for her?
[MAKOTO] Yeah.
[AKANE]
I bet she was very happy.
[AKANE] She is sleeping
in it, afterall.
She was super excited
about it, which made me
really happy.
I think you'll
probably be fine.
Huh?
Isn't it coming up?
Your first status
report to the Society,
since moving here.
Oh...
Yeah. I think I have a lot I can
talk about with the Society.
That's good to
hear, Makoto.
(happy) Oh?
Hey, cut it out. You'll wake
up Chinatsu by doing that.
(inflating)
[MAKOTO] Oh, I'm sorry. Oh?
(wowed)
♪Closing Song♪
Wow...
Akane. Oh!
(snoring)
(cute sleepy snores)
(sighing happily)
(KENNY mewing contently)
[MAKOTO]
Now I have one more
thing I can talk about.