[KEI AND CHINATSU]
Thanks, Mom!
[MAKOTO] Thank you for the meal!
[NANA]
Welcome, everyone
eat up.
♪♪
(Crunch)
Omm!
(Happy sounds)
(Crunching)
[AKANE]
This is mine!
Looks like we'll have
some nice weather today.
Sure does.
[NANA]
Anyhow, Chinatsu,
when you're finished eating,
go and water the garden, please.
'Kay!
Ommm!
Hm?
Hey, girl, nice spot
you got there.
(Mwor)
(Yawning meow)
♪Opening song♪
(Light snoring)
Okay.
Oh!
So that's where this was.
(Rustling)
Wow! This takes me back!
(Meow?)
Hmm... I don't
seem to recall...
What is this map anyway?
Oh, well.
(Clang)
(MROW!)
(Door rattling)
Hm?
(Struggling meows)
Huh?
Huh...
[CHINATSU]
Momma!
I'm heading out for a bit!
[NANA]
Okay. Where ya going?
I don't know!
Huh?
But I'm sure it's
somewhere awesome!
What?!
I'll make sure I get
back here by lunchtime!
Watch out for cars!
Okay!
(Door closes)
(Light panting)
♪♪
Huh?
Ah!
Hmm...
Uh?
What's that?
Did someone get sealed
inside that wood with magic?
♪♪
Huh...
(Dog barking)
Huh?
(Clatter)
(Dog barking)
Huh?
D‐did they fight?
(BARK! BARK!)
AAHHH!
(Tired sigh)
Huh?!
Ah?!
(Rustling)
Wow!
(Gleeful sighs)
Wah! Huh?
Huh?!
Huh...
Hello, my darling.
Huh?
You have something sitting
right on top of your head.
Huh?! D‐don't tell me it's
a caterpillar...
Ugh...
It looks like
it's your lucky day.
You should keep this and make
sure to take good care of it.
There's a magic charm
that says if you catch
a cherry blossom petal
before it hits the
ground and hold on to it,
then the person you
like will like you back.
Aahhh...
Awhile back, I had
a good friend tell me
of that cherry
blossom magic.
(Chuckles)
Hm?
(Turns page)
Oh... I remember when
that happened...
Oh, no!
I don't have time for this.
Oh!
A jar?
I wonder what I
put inside it...
Oh. October 3rd.
Huh?
Let's see...
October 3rd, October 3rd...
Here it is!
(Gasp)
(Rustling)
I must have forgotten
that I had pickled these.
Om. Mmm...
Delicious!
♪♪
Huh?!
[BOY 1]
If we bury it here,
no one will find it.
[BOY 2]
I dunno. I wouldn't be so sure.
Alright, that
should do it, guys.
Huh?!
Ah, a cat!
Huh? You're right!
It's pitch black!
Whose cat is it?
(Worried gasp)
[BOY 3]
Kitty, Kitty!
Ah, it dodged me!
Me too! Ah!
Awesome! It's so cool!
It's a ninja!
[BOY 2]
It's a ninja cat!
(Sassy meow)
[BOYS]
Nin, nin, nin, nin, meow!
(Laughter)
Ah!
Hm?
♪♪
Is she casting a spell?
(Crumble)
AHH!
What in the‐?!
Uh...?
(Scared gasp and screams)
(Fast panting)
She knew I was on to her!
(Happy sounds)
Chito's amazing!
(Joyous giggling)
(Relaxed sigh)
Ah, something smells good.
[NANA]
Lunch is ready!
Wow, this looks
delicious.
[NANA]
Eat up before it gets cold.
[MAKOTO]
Yes, ma'am.
Where's the kid?
She left this morning
to go play somewhere.
She should be back
soon, though.
[MAKOTO]
I brought something down.
Please feel free
to have some.
I pickled these
vegetables myself.
Oh, they look good!
When was that?
It was back on October 3rd.
Uh... Last year?
[CHINATSU]
I'm home! What's for lunch?
Whoa, what happened?
Look at yourself...
Hm?
A secret.
[NANA]
Clean the dirt off your
clothes and come inside.
And wash your hands.
'Kay.
What does she mean
by "a secret"?
I wonder...
[NANA] (Wincing)
So sour!
Huh?
I figured.
(Faucet knob squeaks)
Oh!
Ahh!
Hmm, well, there it goes...
I sure am hungry.
(Door slides open and closed)
(Mwor...)
(Light snoring and grunting)
[MAKOTO]
Chito!
Come on, I'm
ready to go!
Makoto.
Huh?
You going out?
Yeah, I'm going for a walk.
Oh, by yourself?
No, with Chito.
You sure you'll
be okay?
Remember, you have
no sense of direction.
You might not ever
make it back here.
Hey, I'm not really
THAT bad off.
Want me to come
along with you?
No! You don't have to
worry about me, okay?
Besides, Chito is coming
with me, so I'll be fine.
Hm?
Chito has been out
exploring the local area,
so she's got a better lay of the
land than I could ever have.
(Mwor!)
So, you're gonna have her
show you around the town?
That's right.
"Chito GPS."
Yeah? That's
pretty impressive.
(Purring)(Meow!)
I'd expect nothing less.
Huh? Why's she
looking smug?
She says that she was out
there again this morning
surveying the land.
Alright.
Well, take care.
Okay.
[MAKOTO]
I'm heading out!
(Door opens and closes)
Now then, where should
we go looking first?
Chito, you have any recommended
spots for us to see?
(Meow!)
Ah, you know something
interesting?
Where is it?
(Mwor...)
"It's a surprise to
look forward to"?
You must really
like it.
Alright! I can't wait for
you to show me this amazing
new spot of yours, Chito.
(Meow!)
♪♪
Is this it?
(Mwor!)
Huh?
(Mwor...)
Huh! That doesn't look
like me at all!
(Mwor!)
It did when I was
four years old?
(Meow...)
Huh? My face...
looked like that?
(Meow!)
You know of somewhere even
more interesting to go?
♪♪
(Dog barking aggresively)
(Meow.)
Um... this isn't
what I had in mind.
(Dog growling)
Hey...
(Mwor!)
that's not
very nice of you.
(Aggressive barking)
Don't tease him like that just
because he has to be tied up.
(Snarling)
Okay, let's get going!
(Metal clanging)
(Mwor?)
(Barking intensifies)
Huh?
(MWOR!)
Huh?! AHHH!
AHHHH!
(Continued barking)
♪♪
(Heavy panting)
Ah, that really
startled me!
Chito, don't ever do
anything like that again!
(Mwor...)
I don't think a walk has
ever tired me out like this.
(Meow! Mwooor!)
You know of a
better place, huh?
Uh! Hey, wait up!
Oh!
Is this the spot?
(Mwor...)
Huh? Why would
I "hold on"?
For what?
(Rustling)
Wow! I could be showered
with petals all day!
(Mwor...)
Oh?
(Meow!)
Where to now?
Stop running and
wait for me, Chito!
Oh?
(Meow!)
(Meow! Meow!)
Ah!
AH!
(Both scream)
Hey, Nao!
Oh, um... uh...
hey there...
[NAO]
D‐did I surprise you?
You sure did. I thought
you were a scary dog.
A... dog?
Why?
What are you doing
in a place like this?
I'm in the middle
of a walk,
and needed to take
a little break.
You look like you're in the
middle of going somewhere?
Sort of...
I'm actually working.
Ooh! That's pretty generous
of you to help out at the
shop on a Sunday.
No, no, it's not
really like that.
My parents have a little
system where I don't get my
allowance unless I help out.
Oh? Oh, there's a cat.
(Mwor)
Hey. Well, aren't you
a friendly little guy.
I guess this is your
first time meeting her.
So, this is your cat?
Yes, her name's Chito.
Cool. So, witches do really
keep company with black cats.
Some witches have other animal
companions.
Crows or spiders,
for instance.
Wait a sec! What about
that caterpillar?!
Uh, not that one.
Okay.
(Mwor...)
(Sniffing)
(Chuckling) She's cute.
(Purring)
Huh? Oh? What is it?
She says,
"You are cute too."
Um, thank you very much.
You two can understand
each other then?
[NAO]
You sure? I'm just gonna go
there to make a delivery.
It's fine. I didn't have a
set plan for my walk anyway,
so this will be fun.
Is this fine with you Chito?
(Mwor!)
[MAKOTO]
There are a lot of nice
houses around here.
[NAO]
Yeah, I heard that, back
in the day, this farming
district was booming.
It was always super‐busy.
[NAO]
Anyone home?
It's me, Ma'am!
[WOMAN]
I'm on my way!
Thanks for coming!
Thank you for your business.
I have the sake you ordered.
Thanks for always
making deliveries.
My pleasure!
Oh, who might this be?
I haven't seen her before.
This is my friend Makoto.
She just moved to town recently.
It's nice to meet you.
Oh, I see that now.
Nice to meet you.
[WOMAN]
A cat!
Dear me... would you
happen to be a witch?
(Gasp)
Uh... Uhh...
That's ridiculous, Ma'am.
(Nao groans)
I really have no idea what
you're talking about.
There's no such thing
as witches or anything
else that's scary.
Everyone knows that!
(Laughs)
Oh, I figured
you were one.
There's no need to
hide it from me, dear.
(Reluctant sigh)
How did you know I was one?
(Chuckle)
Well, years before
you were born,
I used to be good
friends with a witch.
Huh? Is that
really true?
When I was a lot younger,
I knew a witch much like
yourself who always had
a black cat with her.
We played together
all the time.
But after I
finally got married,
I lost all contact and
never heard from her again.
What kind of person was she?
She was a regular girl
just like you are now, dear.
She was fond
of magic charms
and taught me quite a few
of them back in our heyday.
Magic charms...?
Uh?
Let me tell you a secret...
It was thanks to one
of her magic charms
that I was able to
finally marry my husband.
So cool! A charm for falling
in love?! What is it?
Good question...
Well, I tried so many
that I have no idea
which one was the
winning magic charm.
(Chuckles)
Oh, well that's kinda
too bad you don't know.
Is there someone you
have feelings for, Nao?
Huh? No, no, not really.
Oh...
[NAO]
Chito GPS, huh?
So, where did
she take you?
Hmm, it's a long story.
(Meow!)
What is it?
This time, are you
really going to take us
somewhere interesting?
(Mwor!)
Can I maybe come
with you guys?
Of course.
Huh.
[NAO]
There she is!
(Mwooor!)
Oh?
Oh? You plan on digging here?
Hm?
(Digging and scraping)
Oh!
Now this looks like it could
be quite interesting!
(Mwor...)
[BOTH]
Hmm...
(Gasp)
[NAO]
Is this... a time capsule?
Huh?!
(Mwooor...)
Chito, don't go messing
around with this!
This must be very
important to someone.
(Disgruntled meow)
I wonder who...
[MAKOTO]
Hey, everyone!
Welcome home.
Looks like you managed
to make it back.
Yeah, somehow.
(Tired sigh)
[KEI]
You seem tired.
Yeah, it was a
really long day.
Seems Chinatsu's tired, too.
She's still napping.
(Light snoring)
[MAKOTO]
She just twitched.
Maybe she dreamt she
fell down the stairs.
Maybe she fell in
a pitfall instead.
(Snoring and grunting)
Akane's been sleeping
too much, don't you agree?
Yeah.
(Light snoring)
(Meowing yawn)
♪Closing song♪