♪♪
(Uncomfortable sigh)
[AKANE]
How are you doing?
Ah. I‐I'm done.
[AKANE]
You can't go
any longer?
I can't, that's
all I've got left.
(Sigh)
Flying really hurts
my butt and thighs
if I'm sitting up
there for too long.
(Hysterical laugh)
All witches deal
with that.
Oh, is it that common?
Really? Other witches seem
fine flying for long periods.
[MAKOTO]
Hmm... I wonder if there's
another way to ride.
You've got it all wrong.
Give me the broom.
Here's the secret:
Don't put all your weight
on top of it, Makoto.
Huh? I don't understand
what you mean.
[AKANE]
Come on, you'll catch on.
Try and watch carefully?
Mm‐hmm.
Oh, now I get it!
Many witches tend to
think they need to ride
on top of their brooms
but really, you should
be trying to levitate
your whole body like this.
I understand now!
It was painful because
I was just trying to
levitate my broom.
Hm?
[AKANE]
Exactly.
You only need to lightly
touch your broom.
I see...
Your broom is just a tool
that clears away gravity,
so just keep that in
mind when you fly around.
[MAKOTO]
Okay.
Well, that's new.
♪Opening song♪
[MAKOTO]
Okay, time for
more practice.
Let's see what I can do!
Hmmm...
Hey, Chinatsu...
Huh?
A bet you didn't know...
witches once flew with
things other than brooms.
Like pigs.
What?!
Yeah, they flew on
top of them for sure!
Pretty weird!
Wha‐? So cool!
You think that's cool?
For sure!
(Laughs)
Well, I guess so.
Kei...
what have you been
doing over there?
Hm?
I'm just weeding.
(Snap)
Yep, I've been weeding Makoto
and I's vegetable field.
So I thought I'd take
the opportunity to start
weeding around the house too.
(Laughs)
I've never seen a high
school boy willingly doing
farm work on the weekends.
You're a real strange
one, aren't you?
[KEI]
So what?
Akane, you're one to talk,
dropping out of high school
so you can head off
to Hong Kong like that.
Huh?!
Well, I just really wanted
to meet Jackie so badly...
"Jackie"?
Just need to lightly touch it.
I know I can do this.
(Hearty sigh)
Akane, how long do you
plan on staying around?
Hmm... I'm done traveling
for the moment,
so I'm gonna take
it easy for awhile.
Does that mean you're going
to stay with us again tonight?
It does. I plan on staying
for several days.
For real?!
Most definitely.
You wanna play some
cards together again?
(Gleeful gasp)
Yippee!
(Chuckle)
Yay! Akane's gonna
stay with us!
(Cheering continues)
Oh my God, can I please
seriously have her?!
She's just too cute!
Um... I gotta check
with my parents.
(Laughing)
Yay!
(Laughing stops)
Huh?
Please make me
your apprentice.
Uh!
Please train me to be a witch!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[KEI]
Chinatsu, do you
really mean that?
Of course, I do.
After spending time
with Makoto and Akane,
I've realized how cute and
amazing witches truly are!
I want to become one
so I can do awesome
magic and fly around
doing super cool stuff!
Please, please make me
your loyal apprentice!
And teach me the ways
of your worldly magic!
Hmm...
(Anxious sigh)
Does an ordinary girl
even have a chance
to become a witch?
It's not impossible.
Oh, yeah! I can become a witch!
Don't get excited.
This is a rather
important decision you
need to think about.
It's not something we can just
decide between ourselves.
(Kei chuckles)
[AKANE]
First, go and see what your mom
and dad have to say, alright?
Then we'll decide after that.
Alright! I understand!
Is this a problem?
Hmm, maybe a bit...
It's quite difficult for
a regular person to try
and become a witch.
(Chinatsu giggles)
[AKANE]
Worst case scenario,
it becomes impossible
to lead a normal life.
[AKANE]
I'm pretty sure your mother
is aware of all that.
(Washer beeps)
Mom!
Yes?
I want to talk to you about
something very important.
Oh? What is it, sweetie?
[CHINATSU]
Well...
So, she said, "Wow, a witch?!
You should go for it!"
[BOTH]
Huh?!
And on the phone, Dad
said that sounds cool!
(Laughs)
I see your parents are just
as open‐minded as ever, huh?
So, you'll make
me your apprentice?
Um... I'm not really
taking apprentices right now,
so I don't wanna just
casually say "sure."
But...
Akane, please!
I'm begging you!
I wanna be
made of magic too!
Nice groveling...
Hmm...
(Pleading groans)
[AKANE]
Alright. How about
we do this, Chinatsu?
Starting now, I'll begin
to show you all sorts
of different things.
[CHINATSU]
Will it be many things?
Yes, many, many things.
Compared to what
you've already seen,
I'll give you a
little deeper look
into what goes on
within the
witch's world.
Uh!
[AKANE]
I'll introduce you to
the jobs witches can do,
how they have fun,
their different rituals,
and what other witches
are like besides us!
[AKANE]
You wanna know that?
I do!
I'll find the opportunities for
you to experience all that.
After you get a feel
for how witches live,
you can decide if you
really want to become one.
Hmm...
Sure, let's do that.
'Kay...for the time being,
you are to become an
apprentice witch and learn
our everyday lifestyle.
[KEI]
Hey, good for you.
Congratulations.
You're a witch now, Chinatsu.
You may be an apprentice,
but you're a full witch.
I look forward to your
instruction, Master!
(Laughs)
[MAKOTO]
(Straining groans)
(Sigh)
I think I'm starting to
get the hang of this now.
Hey there, Chinatsu.
Look at what I can do.
I'm able to levitate
a bit longer.
Are you ready to see it?
Makoto.
Yes? What is it?
(Inhale)
Greetings!
I look forward to studying
alongside you, Master!
Huh?
[MAKOTO]
Um, same to you, Chinatsu.
♪♪
[MAKOTO] (Sigh)
It kind of took
me by surprise.
You becoming a
witch, I mean.
Oh?
I'm an
apprentice.
You may be an
apprentice,
but it's still good news
for the witch community
since recruitment is down.
Oh, that's a shame.
But you must remember...
telling other people
you've become a witch
is off the table...
Mm‐hmm, I'll
tell no one.
[MAKOTO]
Well, not that I'm
really one to talk...
True.
(Footsteps)
[CHINATSU]
Hey, Makoto.
After you're a witch,
what are you supposed to
do with all your powers?
It's not really
set in stone per se.
You can basically do
just about anything.
Hm... Anything I want?
Yep. For example, you could
dabble in medicine and sell it.
Or play around with
the different spells.
You could become a
fortune teller like Inukai.
Or you could choose to
travel all around the world
like my sister.
It's up to each witch to
decide her desired path.
Cool!
But... just don't do
anything mean‐spirited.
Well, what path do
you plan on taking?
That's a good question. Hmm...
I don't really know.
To be honest, I haven't
completely decided yet...
But ideally I'd like to help
those around me
while being the best witch
I can possibly be...
or close to that.
Wow! You'll be
a super hero!
Oh no, not me.
You're being way too kind.
Chinatsu, what do
you want to do?
Oh!
Uh...
First, learn all
the magic...
Ah! Then I want to summon
a pumpkin carriage!
(Warping)
Wow!
After that, I'll take
control of all the toys!
(Marching)
[MAKOTO]
Amazing! (Giggles)
Then I'll summon a house
made of yummy candy!
(Warping)
Sounds good! I think that's
just wonderful!
(Giggles)
Then...
it will eat anyone who
dares to try and go inside!
Munchie, munchie, munchie,
munchie, munchie! Mmm...
Huh?!
(Giggles)
Just kidding!
I'll think about what
I wanna do! (Laughs)
Huh...
(Dramatic music)
(Thunder)
[BOTH]
Huh?
Are you some kind
of film buff?
[KEI]
I wouldn't go that far,
but I do like movies.
You know, Kei, I was
once cast in a movie.
Seriously?! Sweet!
Which movie?
(Laughs)
It was minor.
The title's embarrassing,
so it's my secret.
You're sure full
of crazy mysteries.
[KEI]
Well, I guess I'll check
out this one next.
Hey, we made it back.
Hey there, Akane.
Welcome back, you two.
Did you buy the stuff?
[MAKOTO]
Yes, we got everything
you asked us to.
Alright then.
Why don't we get started?
Welcome to Akane's Intro
to Magic Course: Lesson 2!
Applause.
[BOTH]
Oh, wow!
So what kind of magic will we
be learning this time?
This lesson will be a riot.
Today we are going to be
making some suspect snacks.
[KEI]
Hm?
Please excuse the bad pun
I just made you
two endure, okay?
[AKANE]
To begin, please place
this sheet over the table.
[MAKOTO AND CHINATSU]
Okay.
One, two, three.
Okay, now draw a
pentagram on this sheet.
Sure thing.
(POP)
(Marker squeaking)
Pentagraph...?
Whoa, it's a star!
Oh, nice!
You drew that really well
without using a ruler.
I started practicing
when I was young.
It's required of witches.
Teach me how to!
Are you finished yet?
(Sizzling)
[AKANE]
Done.
Okay, now please follow my
lead and place one candle
at each of the points
of your pentagram.
Right.
This is a bit dangerous
for you, Chinatsu,
so sit back for now.
'Kay!
(Chuckles)
[AKANE]
You've now learned how to
complete a basic magic circle.
Okay...
Now check the
compass bearings.
And place the snacks you
brought onto the northern
and southern sides.
Alright. Place your
hands over the circle.
And begin to
chant out loud:
"Please bless these snacks
and grant them power."
And repeat.
This is all really cool!
Right... I'll try it.
Let me see if I have everything.
"Please bless these snacks
and grant them power."
Hmm...
(Anxious sigh)
Hm?
Oh. Now leave it be until
the candle burns out.
(Disappointed sighs)
I didn't expect magic
to be so dull.
The flashy stuff is
way more difficult;
they need a bit more practice.
[CHINATSU]
Huh...?
Seriously now...
These candles are
taking a while to burn.
Yeah. I wonder
what'll happen
when they burn out.
[CHINATSU]
Maybe something big
and scary will appear.
Oh, I know! The snacks
are a sacrifice!
Well... you never know!
I wish they'd
burn out already!
Ah. If the flame goes out before
it's done, the magic is ruined.
Ruined?!
Yep.
[AKANE]
If a single flame goes out,
the whole thing's a failure.
(Muffled)
Please don't go out,
please don't go out...
(Groaning)
(Chuckles)
(Groaning continues)
I don't think you
need to worry about
holding your breath.
(Tires squealing on TV)
[MAKOTO]
That's it! When making
a magic circle,
you'll draw the
outer circle first.
[CHINATSU] (Groan)
It's not very good.
Try to concentrate and draw it
all at once without stopping.
Okay.
One more time.
First I do this,
and then I do that...
That's the way.
(Marker squeaking)
Lookie!
[MAKOTO]
Nicely done!
(Giggles)
(Fizzle)
Oh, Akane, look,
they've all burnt out now.
Oh! The spell's
complete, then.
[AKANE]
Okay.
Now, whoever eats these snacks
will be under the effects
of a VERY powerful
witch's spell.
Oh!
Let's not waste any time...
(Rip)
Here.
Huh?!
Uhh... You really...
expect me to eat some?
Of course!
When you're first learning
a new spell,
it's best to try and
experience the effects
of your creation firsthand.
Is that what you always try
and do for your spells?
(Laughs)
Oh no, not me!
What?!
Hmm...
[AKANE]
Here.
Hmm...
[AKANE]
It'll be alright.
It won't kill you.
[CHINATSU]
Come on, Makoto!
Ahh...
Om.
(Snapping)
(Chuckles)
(Sigh)
(Anxious breath)
Hm?
Huh...
I don't think I really feel
any different at all...
(Laughs)
Okay, okay!
Go take a look at that movie
Kei's watching on television.
Sure.
(Tires squealing)
(Loud explosion)
(Chuckles)
(Debris crashing)
(Worried breaths)
(Whimpering)
It exploded all over!
(Crying)
Ah!
Huh?
(Laughs)
It's working!
[MAKOTO]
What's going on? Why do
I feel so incredibly sad!
(Sniffling)
Eating those snacks causes
you to cry at anything!
[AKANE]
The spell is meant to make
someone burst into tears no
matter what they look at.
You gotta be kidding me!
(Sobbing)
(Akane laughs)
[AKANE]
Sorry, sorry.
It'll wear off
in an hour or so.
Too long!
[NANA]
I'm home!
(Crying)
Hey, how does beef
stew sound for dinner?
Huh?
(Whimpering)
Oh?
(Laughs)
She's under a bit of a powerful
spell, as you can see, Nana.
[MAKOTO] (Crying)
I love... beef stew!
(Sobbing)
That sounds great!
You're so happy you're
crying tears of joy.
Beef stew it is!
Make it stop...
(Laughs)
Amazing!
Can I please try
eating some of these?
Chinatsu, you're up
for the challenge?
Sure, go ahead!
(Crying continues)
Om!
(Chewing)
(Machine gun fire)
(Snicker)
(Hysterical laugh)
He's shooting so much!
Hm?
These seem to have the opposite
effect of making someone cry.
(Both laugh)
[AKANE]
Chinatsu, Chinatsu,
try looking at Makoto.
Ah, I think it may have
subsided for a bit.
AHAHA! She's crying!
(Uncontrollable laughter)
(Uncontrollable crying)
(Chito meows)
Chito's nose is so
shiny and adorable!
(Laughter continues)
(Mwooor?)
Kenny is really
pretty and shiny, too!
(Sobbing continues)
(Laughing)
Chito's tail looks like the
hiragana character "shi"!
Ahahaha!
(Annoyed meow)
Kenny's tail looks like a "J"!
(Confused meow)
(Laughing and crying continue)
[MAKOTO]
Don't laugh at me!
(Kei groans)
They're so loud.
(Stifled laughs)
(Stifled sobs)
(Both suffering)
[NANA]
Can you chop this for me?
Sure.
(Whimpering)
Ahhhh...
AHAHAHA! She's crying
before she's cut into it!
Chinatsu, let's have
a staring contest.
First one to laugh loses, 'kay?
One, two, three!
Mhmhmhm!
(Struggling)
(Hysterical laugh)
Your face looks so funny!
You lose, Chinatsu!
Now hand me the bowl, please.
Thank you for that, my sweet.
Okay, one more time.
One, two, three!
Ohohoho!
(Both laugh)
You lose again!
Go wipe down the table.
(Laughter continues)
You look like you're
having fun, Nana.
(Laughs)
(Crying)
(Dramatic music on TV)
Wassup?
Hi, Dad!
Huh?
(Keiji grunting)
Hm?
(Hysterical laugh)
(Sobbing)
(Laughing)
Looks like he ate
both of them...
(Hysterical laughing and crying)
♪Closing song♪