♪♪
Hmm.
[FEMALE VOICE]
Kenny...
(Mwor?)
What year is it
right now?
(Mwor)
In AD, I mean.
(Mwor mwor‐mwor)
Wow, already?
That means she's probably
already moved out on her own.
(Mwor?)
That girl. I swear.
(Heavy sigh)
I wonder if she's doing well.
Alright!
Let's go check up on her!
(Mwor!)
♪Opening song♪
(TV jingle)
[NEWS ANCHOR]
And now for today's weather.
Looks like its time to
start pulling out your
warm‐weather clothes.
The string of warm weather
we've been having lately
is expected to continue with
more of the same today.
(Anchor continues)
[MAKOTO]
Oh, hi! There you are.
Huh?
Hm?
There's something I
want to ask you about.
Is now a good time?
Yeah, what's up?
Uncle, I was thinking
I would like to study
the use of plants as part
of my witch's training.
You want to study... plants?
Yes. I would like to try
and grow some vegetables.
"Vegetables"?
Yes sir. I was wondering if
you have a field I could use.
I don't mind at all if it's
small and needs clearing.
Let me think.
Well, um...
(Thick, country accent)
You can take a gander at
that small patch out yonder.
Ain't nobody tended to
'em there weeds out back,
so ya hafta root out
a whole bunch of 'em.
Uhh...
Out in that shed, I got
me a hoe an' a shovel,
so have at those, if ya want.
Also got a bit of fertilizer
there, so help yerself.
So, um...
He said that we've got
an unused field at the
back of the house
that you can try and use.
He said there are also
some tools you can take.
O‐oh, I see!
(Kei laughs)
Oh, yeah?
Dad definitely does
have a thick accent.
I'll need to get used
to listening to him.
You'll get the hang of it
the more you're around him.
Here's a watering can.
I sure hope I'm able too.
Don't worry about it.
Now, we still need...
this...
But I do kind
of feel bad.
Hm?
About you having to
help me out like this.
Oh, no problem.
I have nothing but
free time today.
And as the son of a farmer,
I need to start learning
about this kind of stuff.
This will be a really awesome
opportunity for us.
Do you want to
become a farmer too?
Hmm...
Good question, Makoto.
Being the eldest, it's
definitely something that I
need to consider for the future.
But my parents said
not to stress over it
and do whatever I love.
Wow. You've got
great parents.
I sure do.
Okay, here it is.
Wow!
Uh... where is it?
You're looking right at it.
But it's covered
in thick grass.
[KEI]
Grandma used to tend to it,
but since she's passed away,
no one has bothered
to take care of it.
That's such a shame.
Clearing all of it
would be difficult...
so let's just till
this one area.
Okay!
(Struggling grunt)
Ah!
Ouchie...
(Struggling grunt)
Ah!
Ouchie...
(Struggling grunt)
(Kei sighs)
Ah!
Ow...
[CHINATSU]
Kei...
Huh?
Do you need
any help?
Yeah... we really do.
(Struggling grunt)
Well... Makoto could
at least use your help.
Looks like she's
having a hard time.
Ah!
Okay.
Ouch... Ouch... Ouch...
I'm here to help.
Oh, that's very thoughtful
of you, Chinatsu. Oh?
[MAKOTO]
I see Chito has tagged along.
She follows me.
It seems like you two are
really getting along together.
We're good buddies.
(Mrow!)
(Giggle)
[CHINATSU]
So, do all witches have to
grow vegetables like you are?
Sort of. To be full‐fledged,
witches need to accumulate
this knowledge...
If I want to be recognized...
(Struggling)
...this is what I'll have to...
DO!
(Sigh)
[MAKOTO]
Growing vegetables will serve
as both a good life experience
and part of my training.
Ooh...
What kind of vegetables
do you like the most?
[CHINATSU]
I don't really
like vegetables...
[KEI]
Alright! It looks like
we're done weeding.
It goes a lot faster
with three people.
Makoto, Chinatsu, let's
take a little break.
[BOTH]
'Kay!
(Bird cries)
(Gasp)
(Amazed gasp)
(CAW!)
AHH!
(Cawing continues)
(Gleeful gasp)
Uh, hey! Kei?
Huh?
There's a strange
bird here.
Hmm...
Oh, that's just
a pheasant.
"Pheasant"?
You mean the bird in the
folktale of "Momotaro"?
That's it.
We see a lot of them
pretty often out here.
Is this you're first one?
Yes!
I never knew that's the
sound pheasants make.
So pretty!
Ah!
Almost!
I know how you feel.
I try to catch them too.
Well, not me.
(Panting)
(Wings fluttering)
[KEI]
Heh. She's tilling
the soil for us.
(Weak panting)
(Long, heavy breaths)
Makoto!
You should probably take
a lunch break soon!
Or you'll be too tired!
O‐okay...
(Sigh)
That pheasant sure is a
fast little bird, isn't it?
But still I felt like I was
so close to catching it.
You really want to
catch it that bad?
Wow, I've never seen
anyone committed to the
chase as you've been.
I do! This is my first one!
It's a rare thing for me!
And there aren't
any in Yokohama!
Uh... Okay...
It teases me by staying so
close, yet still too far.
[MAKOTO]
Taunting me with those
eyes that seem to say,
"Catch me if you can!"
(Kei and Chinatsu sigh)
Cousin? Is catching
a pheasant
also part of your
training as a witch?
Huh?! No,
not at all.
It has nothing to do
with me being a witch.
I just want
to catch it.
[CHINATSU]
Ohh...
Huh?
[KEI]
Looks like
Chito wants it.
[CHINATSU]
You're right! Go get it!
(Mrow...)
(Sheen)
(Furious meowing)
(Laughing)
You're silly, Chito!
You're just running back
and forth like a loon!
(Both sigh)
(Sad meow)
[KEI]
Well, back to work we go.
'Kay.
Got it.
Alright!
This time, I'll be
sure to catch it!
[KEI]
Hey, I think you've lost
sight of our goal here.
(CAW!)
(Heavy thud)
[KEI]
Time to spread the garden
lime and fertilizer.
(Chinatsu and Makoto agree)
[KEI]
We'll use the hoe to
mix them into the soil.
Let's work hard together
until we're all done.
[BOTH]
Okay!
♪♪
[KEI]
Alright, the
soil's good to go.
(Happy laugh)
Now we leave it be
for a week or two.
Why can't we
start planting now?
We need to wait
for the lime and
fertilizer to settle.
There's nothing we
can do until then.
(Dejected)
Oh...
That makes sense.
What vegetables do
you wanna grow?
Ah, good question.
I still need to give
it some thought.
Well, summer vegetables
would be best now that
it's spring time.
Eggplants, cucumbers, tomatoes,
corn, and pumpkins, okras,
bell peppers, garlic,
bitter melons, zucchinis,
chives, green beans,
jute mallows, and can't
forget Japanese ginger...
Oh, I almost forgot
about the herbs!
Rosemary, sage,
sweet basil, and
some chamomile...
Hey, we don't have
enough land.
[KEIJI]
Oh, you're really
gettin' at it.
[ALL]
Hmm?
[MAKOTO]
Hi, Uncle!
How is it?
Oh!
Lookin' good!
Yes!
We did our
very best.
If there's anything
you're not sure about,
now's the time
to ask Dad.
Yup, ask away, kiddo!
There is one thing I've
been wondering about...
I heard there are certain
vegetables you shouldn't
grow near each other.
Is that really true?
Yeah, that's right...
There's a number of 'em
that can sure get‐
OH! Pheasant!
Ah!
Makoto, never seen
a pheasant, have ya?!
Yes, I...
Hold it right there,
you pheasant!
I'm gonna get ya real good!
(Pheasant caws)
Hey! Wait!
Tryin' to make a
fool of me, eh?!
Looks like Pa is committed
to the chase too.
[KEIJI]
...then I'm gonna catch ya!
Seriously...
(Pheasant caws)
You ain't gonna best me!
You wanna piece of this?!
Hey, come back!
(Chinatsu humming)
[FEMALE VOICE]
Oh, those are some
nice petunias!
Ah. Huh?
Ahh...
You've really
grown, Chinatsu.
How have you been?
[CHINATSU]
I'm fine...
Glad to hear it!
(Meow!)
So, is she home
right now?
Who are you talking about?
Makoto.
She hasn't...
come back home yet.
Well, what about your mom?
Mom's here...
Good!
I guess I'll wait inside
until Makoto comes back.
This brings back
some memories!
(Laughs)
Nana!
[NANA]
Yes?
Long time no see!
How have you been?
[NANA]
Who are you?!
Why can't we get
normal visitors?
[KEI]
My personal recommendation is
probably the cherry blossoms.
[MAKOTO]
Oh, the Cherry Blossom
Festival sounds great!
Well, in that case, we can
just go after school sometime.
[MAKOTO]
Huh? You want to
go on a weekday?
Wouldn't it be
best to go on one
of our days off?
Actually, it gets really
packed on the weekends
with tourists and such,
so it's hard to enjoy it.
Ah, that makes sense.
I haven't been to
the Festival since
elementary school.
Huh?
I'm so excited!
(Mrow...)
Oh! Hi, Kenny!
I didn't see you there.
Wait! What the‐?!
You're slow...
[MAKOTO]
Wh‐What is Kenny doing
here at the house?
Kei!
[KEI]
How should I know...?
I win!
ARGH!
You got me!
Second time in a row!
[MAKOTO]
Huh?!
AHH! No way!
Big Sister?!
Huh?
(Grunting)
Long time no see, Makoto.
Uh...
Sister...
What are you doing
here at the house?
Huh?
[AKANE]
Playing Old Maid.
No... that's not
what I meant.
Oh, hi, Kei!
You've gotten so big
since the last time.
Have you been
doing alright?
Hi! Yeah, I'm good.
It's been a while.
Why the sudden
visit here?
Mm‐hmm...
(Laughs)
I couldn't help wondering
how my cute little
sister was doing here.
So I came to see!
Jeez... You
surprised me.
If you're gonna come
and visit, you should
contact me ahead of time.
Sorry about that!
The idea to visit just suddenly
popped into my head!
[CHINATSU]
'Scuse me.
Huh?
Are you a flying witch
like your sister?
Mm! That's right.
(Happy squeal)
My big sister here is quite
famous in the world of witches.
Even among her fellow witches,
she is recognized for being
extremely talented.
(Laughs)
Oh, I'm not all that
famous, Lil Sis...
Wait, maybe I am...
(Laughs)
[KEI]
So, are you still on
your wandering journey?
Hm! Yeah, I am.
Lately, I've been
bouncing around Africa.
Oh, I almost forgot!
I brought you some presents
all the way from there too!
[CHINATSU]
Yay!
Oh, what did ya get?
[AKANE]
Here. For Chinatsu, I have a
cacao pod I got in Ghana.
Uhh...
You can make
chocolate with it!
For Makoto, I have some
rock salt I from Mali.
Oh...
You can break it up with a
hammer and use it for cooking!
For Kei, I have some crude
oil I found in Libya.
Mmm...
I'm not really sure what you
should do with it.
[KEI]
All of this stuff
is unprocessed...
You remember, she's never
been good at giving gifts.
Hmm...
And...
for Nana, I brought some
green coffee beans.
(Satisfied chuckle)
[KEI]
Well, make yourself at home.
Okay, thanks!
[CHINATSU]
Can we actually
make chocolate?
[KEI]
Hmm, let's give it a try.
[AKANE]
By the way, Makoto...
Yes?
Have I heard correctly...
you haven't used magic
since leaving home?
Ah! Wh‐where did
you hear that...?
From our little friend here.
(Mrow)
(Prolonged groan)
She said all you've done
is fly on your broom.
And that was just once.
Is that true?
(Echoing)
Uh... Yes...
It's just as you say...
I'm sorry...
Oh, that's okay.
It's not something you
have to apologize for.
Unlike me, you're not the
type of witch who has to
rely solely on her magic.
You should be able to learn and
cast spells on your own pace.
Anyway, that's my opinion
as your big sister.
(Sigh)
That being said,
magic gets rusty
if you don't
use it that often.
Even just keeping
up with a few basic
practices is enough.
Got it?
Understood!
Good! Well, how about I teach
you an easy spell right now?
We'll warm up with
something you can ease into.
(Cats conversing)
[AKANE]
Chinatsu!
[CHINATSU]
Yes?
What is it?
We need your help.
Is there a place around
here we won't be seen?
Um... A place you
two won't be seen...?
You won't be seen
in most places.
There aren't many
people here.
[AKANE]
In the olden days, this spell
was often used by witches.
It's super simple,
so it's an ideal practice
for beginner witches to try.
Chinatsu, are you
going to watch?
Yeah, I want to
see some magic!
(Crackling)
[AKANE]
I'll go first to show
you how it's done.
Chinatsu, can I please
have one or two strands
of your hair?
You want my hair?
Huh...
Will this be enough?
Yep, thank you.
Now, we put your
hair inside...
and write the spell here.
[AKANE]
This magic requires hair
from a girl with black hair.
So, my hair wouldn't work
since it's not black.
Next, you throw
it into the fire.
(Crackling)
And let it burn until
it turns in to ash.
Then...
...use water to put
out the fire out!
(Sizzling)
(Both gasp)
(Smoke hissing softly)
Is it done?
What's it do?
They're on their way now,
so don't you worry at all.
Chinatsu, try holding
up your arm like this.
My arm?
(CAW!)
(Both gasp)
Ahh! Whoa! It's a crow!
(Cawing)
Yep. This spell will summon
crows to wherever you are.
The smoke acts as a marker
to draw the crows to you.
I heard long ago that witches
hired to fight in wars
often used crows to carry out
reconnaissance on the enemy.
Wow! Who'd have thought?
So cool!
Okay, Little Sister,
now you give it a try.
Right, I'll give it a go!
[MAKOTO]
For the hair, is it
okay to use my own?
Sure, any black hair
will do fine.
(Crackling)
Now you just need to put out
the fire with water.
It really is
quite simple.
(POOF)
Ah!
Huh?
Uh‐oh...
It seems pretty black...
[AKANE]
Hm...
(Soft hissing)
(Wings flapping)
(Cawing)
Wow. But it looks like
it's working really well.
(Cawing)
(Cawing increases)
Hm?
(Cawing continues)
Huh?
(Cawing increases)
(CAW!)
Awesome!
Um... Wh‐what...
What's going on here, Sis?
[AKANE]
Hm...
Ah! That must be it!
It is because you used
a witch's hair!
It's way too powerful.
You should probably use a
regular person's next time.
(Laughs hysterically)
But you said I could
use my hair...
Big Sister?
I need to get going
pretty soon.
HUH?!
What should I do
with all these guys?
[AKANE]
They'll fly off
eventually.
Huh? Leave them alone?
See ya, Makoto.
Try to keep up with
your training, okay?
See ya, Chinatsu!
You're leaving already?
Yeah, I have a
camel waiting for me.
"A camel"?
I'll stop by again sometime
soon, alright? See ya!
(Wind picks up)
[CHINATSU]
Huh...
Your sister came and
went like a typhoon.
Yeah...
♪Closing song♪