♪♪
(Stall beeps)
(Bus doors close)
♪Opening song♪
Oh?
(Amazed gasp)
(PA dings)
Stop requested.
(Gasp)
Ooh!
(Gleeful laugh)
Chito, look at that!
It's April and there's
still so much snow left.
Hah! It's cold!
Looks good... I wonder if
it would be okay to eat it.
(Disgruntled meow)
[KEI]
Makoto?
Ah? Huh?
I knew it was you.
Long time no see.
Oh, is that really you, Kei?
It just can't be!
You've grown up so much
I could hardly recognize
it was actually you.
It's me. Why are you standing
there holding a snowball?
Uh... Well,
this is, uh...
No reason, really.
(Snow crunches)
(Chito meows)
[KEI]
Hey, Chito.
(Meow)
How have ya been?
Wow! You've grown a lot too.
(Sad meow)
Are you here to show
me back to your place?
Yeah. I remember
you get lost easily
I thought it would be best
if I just came to pick you up.
(Laughs)
You didn't have to
bring that up, Kei.
It was such a long time ago.
Well, let's go.
I can't wait!
It's been so long since
I've seen Chinatsu!
(Chuckles)
Makoto! My house
isn't that way!
Huh?!
[MAKOTO]
Hey, Chinatsu.
Huh?
Hmm. How are
you doing?
I'm fine... thanks.
It's been a
while, Chinatsu.
Do you remember
who I am, sweetie?
Uhh...
My brother's girlfriend?
No...
Whoa! Ah! It's a cat!
(Meow)
[KEI]
Chinatsu, I doubt
you'll remember.
Huh?
After all, you were
only three the last time
the both of you met.
This woman, she's
your real mother.
Huh?!
Mommy!
No! That's not true!
I'm not your mom!
Is she a freeloader?
No. Let me introduce
you to Makoto Kowata.
She's gonna live with us.
She's one of our relatives;
a second cousin in the family.
Hmm?
It's nice to meet you again.
Oh! Is this the person that Mom
was telling us about earlier?
Yeah, that's right.
The one who
always gets lost?
The same one.
(Ding)
[KEI]
Well, this is
your room over here.
(Happy gasp)
[MAKOTO]
Looks like all
my boxes arrived.
[KEI]
Uh... Yeah, but don't you
think this is too much stuff?
Not at all! This is completely
normal for a girl my age.
Is that so?
Mm‐hmm!
[KEI]
I'm gonna go get lunch ready.
Come on down when you're ready.
[MAKOTO]
Alright!
(Stretching grunt)
(Sigh)
(Meow?)
Yeah, I'm a bit
tired as well.
How are you doing
with all this, Chito?
(Mrow...)
Yeah.
Well, you've always
had such good stamina.
By the way, I'm going
to go shopping later.
You wanna come with me?
(Meow!)
[MAKOTO, MUFFLED]
I swear, you're
such a homebody.
You'll get fat
again, you know.
(Mrow...)
(Scared groan)
Well, do you want me
to buy you anything?
(Excited meow)
(Panting)
(Bubbling)
Brother!
Did you give
her the futon?
Uh‐huh.
But, I...
Yeah?
How long is she
staying with us?
Hmm...
I don't know all the
full details about it,
but I guess...
until she's
full‐fledged to go.
What do you mean?
Is something
bothering you?
Well, no, but...
I get the feeling she's
a dangerous person!
Huh?
It's just that...
I heard her talking to her cat,
and I thought that she‐
[MAKOTO]
Oh, smells good.
Eh!
Are you
making curry?
Yeah, it's just
leftovers from yesterday.
Curry always tastes better when
you let it sit for a day or two.
[KEI]
What about Chito?
Oh... She's dieting again,
so she isn't bothering
with lunch today.
Huh?
What's the matter, Chinatsu?
Uh!
Uh...
(Panting)
Huh?
What's with her?
(News jingle on TV)
(Suspicious groan)
Huh?
Hm!
(News anchor talks
about weather)
Huh?
Hm!
What's wrong, Chinatsu?
Are you okay?
Everything is fine.
I'm just watching TV.
But the TV
is over there.
[ANCHOR]
It's been an
unseasonably warm day...
Oh! I almost forgot...
Hmm?
Is there a general store
or something nearby here?
Let me think...
There's a home improvement
center not far away.
What are you gonna buy?
There's some everyday
stuff I still need.
I was thinking of going
and getting all that.
All those boxes
and you need more?
Yes!
Ah, well that place
is a bit far.
You might get lost
if you go on your own.
Come on, I'll be fine.
No need to worry.
How far is it?
[KEI]
Twenty minutes by foot.
[MAKOTO]
Oh. I actually might get lost.
(Chinatsu groans)
[KEI]
I'll just have Chinatsu
take you there.
HUH?!
Is that alright
with you?
It's fine.
Huh?!
You said you
were free today.
Did I say that?
But what about you?
Well, I've got some things to
take care of, so I can't go.
[KEI]
Makoto isn't very familiar
with the local area,
show her around a bit.
(Groan)
Alright. I'll do it if
she promises to buy me some
donuts while we're there.
Watch your manners!
It's fine. I really don't
mind doing that at all.
Let me buy her some donuts
for all the trouble.
Hold on!
I want to have
delicious donuts too!
[MAKOTO]
(Relaxed sigh)
Beautiful. It sure
is nice around here.
This place puts me at ease.
It makes time feel like
it's going by slowly.
Where did you
come from, Makoto?
Hm? Do you mean
my hometown?
Mm‐hmm.
I come from a place
called Yokohama.
Have you heard of it?
Yes! I know Yokohama!
It's over in Tokyo,
isn't it?
Well, it's very
close to Tokyo.
Wow!
This place is huge!
Chinatsu, to avoid getting
lost, don't leave my side
for a second.
Who's getting lost?
♪♪
Let's see, I
still need... uh...
(Happy gasp and squeal)
(Happy sigh)
[CHINATSU]
I want this one!
And this one for
my big brother!
Those look to be pretty high
in calories and fat.
Chito is going to
be so jealous of us.
So, which one?
Ah, I really like this one!
You do?
This one is tasty, too!
Hmm, it's hard to choose.
(Gleeful chomp)
Is it delicious?
It's super yummy!
Oh, look!
[MAKOTO]
There they are!
I guess they keep
them outside.
Would you mind holding
this for me, Chinatsu?
You want a broom?
Yep.
Huh?
You never know when having
one might be needed for
where you're going.
Hmm... Hmm...
(Broom creaks)
Hmm...
Wonder if this will work...
(Light breeze)
♪♪
Oh, no! I better watch it.
Little too high.
Hmm...
Um... I guess these bamboo
ones are a little finicky.
Maybe if I use it more,
it'll adjust.
AH?!
Huh?
[NAO]
Your relative is
staying at your place?
[KEI]
Yep.
Is it a boy?
A girl. Same age as us.
I don't like it.
Why wouldn't you?
She's going to the
same school as us,
so I'll introduce you.
If you want to.
What's this relative like?
What's she like?
She's kinda strange.
In a mysterious way?
Uh, what now?
"Mysterious"?
Mysterious like how?
Just wait,
you'll see tomorrow.
[CHINATSU]
Kei!
Hm?
Well, look who
decided to show up!
Hm? What do you mean?
[MAKOTO]
That's it. Put your
feet down gently.
What's goin' on?
You get lost?
[MAKOTO]
No, we saw you from above
and thought we would drop in.
Kei, did you see that?!
We were flying through the sky!
Yeah, I saw you up there.
Were you surprised?
Amazing, amazing, amazing!
(Squealing)
Makoto is super awesome!
Calm down, little sister...
YAY!
Oh!
(Chinatsu continues)
Kei...
Hm?
May I ask
who she is?
Oh, this is Nao Ishiwatari.
Her family owns
the liquor store.
We've been
classmates forever.
[MAKOTO]
She's your friend?
That's right.
(Chinatsu continues)
Hello, it's very
nice to meet you.
I'm Makoto Kowata, and I'll
be serving as a witch here
in your beautiful town.
I might cause trouble
from time to time,
but I do hope that we can get
along and be good friends.
[CHINATSU]
Can you believe it?!
Huh?
Hah?
My cousin is the coolest
person in the world!
Uhh...
[CHINATSU]
Amazing! Amazing!
(Squeals and laughter)
Oh my God! Oh my God!
[NAO]
Huh?
We flew!
Yes!
[KEI]
Makoto! It's time to get going.
Yeah! I'm coming!
Wrong turn.
[CHINATSU]
Meow, meow, meow?
Meow, meow...
[MAKOTO]
I'm sorry!
Huh?
Did I keep you waiting long?
[CHINATSU]
So, do witches get to ride
to school on their broomsticks?
No, we don't!
If you ride one for too long,
it will start to press
into your thighs
and it can become
extremely unpleasant.
You don't actually
need to show her...
(Chatter)
(Yawn)
Hi, Nano!
AH!
Ahh...
(Heavy breathing)
(Door opens)
How are you this
morning, Nano?
Uh... Good morning...
I'm so happy that we get to be
in the same class together.
Uh... yeah, um...
it's really great...
Why are you acting scared?
It's just not like you.
Oh, shut up!
It's not like I'm
actually scared, okay?
(Sigh)
Suddenly seeing someone fly
around in the air on a broom
is enough to confuse
any normal person.
Oh...
Are you serious?
Well, it's like I've
always said now...
"Don't let conventional
wisdom hold you hostage."
You never said that.
Don't try to act cool.
Nano...
Hear me out...
Oh?
If you take away the
fact that I'm a witch,
I'm just a regular girl that
sometimes does weird things.
If it's okay, I hope
we can become friends.
I think you're pretty cool.
Uh...
Huh?
My name isn't "Nano"...
It's actually "Nao."
We can be friends.
(Gasp)
[TEACHER]
Attention! It's time for
the first‐year students
to head to the gym.
[MAKOTO]
I'm so very sorry.
[NAO]
It's fine, really.
Anyway, why did you
come to stay at Kei's?
It's our tradition.
It's a normal custom for
witches to be seen
as responsible adults
when they turn 15.
So when we're old enough, we're
able to leave our homes so that
we can start our own life.
[NAO]
That's impressive.
But my parents say that
nowadays the life of a witch is
full of uncertainties,
so they wanted me to
attend high school first
before heading out.
Huh...
They said that if I stay
with relatives it would give
them some peace of mind.
Jeez, talk about tossing
tradition out the window.
(Laughs)
(Light chuckle)
So...
Ah?
does that mean there's
a fair number of witches
hangin' around?
Yeah, there's quite a bit.
In particular, the Tohoku
region has plenty around.
Yeah?
[MAKOTO]
There's lots of nature
and so many resources.
It's said to be easier
to use magic here,
so it's popular with
beginner witches.
I‐I had no idea.
Huh...?
Oh, wait...
Huh?
A second ago...
you said that there were
a lot of witches
in the Tohoku area,
right?
Yeah...
Okay then...
So why don't any
ordinary people like me
know anything about
their existence?
Does that mean they're keeping
the fact that they're witches
a secret from the
rest of us on purpose?
That's a good question.
I never thought about it.
Besides their family and other
directly connected people‐
Huh?! You tell
me this now?!
Alright, stop.
I've heard enough.
Don't get me mixed up in
any of your strange stuff.
I‐it'll be okay!
It's not like there's
a punishment or anything
for knowing about us!
(Kei snoring)
[MAKOTO]
We're just supposed
to try our best
to keep it a secret is all...
I think...
(Schoolbell rings)
(Chatter)
What? But, Kei, y‐you're
not heading home now?
I already have plans to
go hang out with some of my
buddies from middle school.
I'm sorry, but you go on
and head back with Nao.
Oh...
I already asked her to
take you back to the house.
Hey! Make sure you take
good care of Makoto, okay?
Yeah, sure.
Cool, I'm outta here.
Huh? But, what
am I suppose...
Tell Mom I'll be home
for dinner, alright?
(Sigh)
'Kay, shall we get going?
Uh, sure...
[MAKOTO]
I'm sorry for the trouble.
What do you mean?
Having to take me all
the way to Kei's house.
Well, I mean, he sure
didn't waste any time
heading out with his friends.
He does whatever
he feels like.
I guess that's true.
He hasn't changed a bit
from all those years ago.
(Nao laughs)
[NAO]
Is that so?
Where is...
that smell coming from?
I guess we can't really
expect him to grow up.
Huh? Ah!
(Rustling)
Wait! What are you doing?!
Come on! Your sense of direction
can't be THAT bad, can it?
Huh?
No, it's not like that at all!
There's something I want
to give you as a present.
What sort of present?
I want to apologize for
surprising you yesterday
and give you a token
for our new friendship.
No, really, I'm fine
with all of this.
You don't need to make a big
deal out of it, I mean it.
I do! I want to
say thank you.
You're going out of your way
to take me all the way home
and making sure
I don't get lost.
Really...
Okay, hold on a second.
Like I said...
I'm gonna go find it.
I'll be right back!
Uhh...
It's quite a rare plant,
so I'm sure you'll be
surprised when you see it!
She does whatever she
likes even more than Kei.
(Rustling)
[MAKOTO]
I would think I must be
pretty close by now,
judging by the strong
smell of ammonia in the air.
Oh!
I knew it was here!
[NAO]
Hey, Kitty!
Lookie!
[MAKOTO]
Hey, Nao!
Huh?
I'm going to pull it
out of the ground now,
so please cover
your ears!
What? My ears?
Just what is she doing?
(Sigh)
Right!
Ooo‐kay!
(Straining groans)
The wild ones always have strong
roots fixed to the ground!
(Loud crack)
Yes! Got it!
(Eerie breathing)
(Ear‐splitting scream)
AAHHH!
(Birds screech)
(Scream continues)
Huh?
(Meow?)
Oh?
Hm?
(Scream continues)
(Inaudible partying)
(Scream dissipates)
Huh? What was that noise?
[MAKOTO]
Nao!
Thank you for
waiting on me!
(Creepy groans)
I finally got it.
Whadya think?
Uh...
(Groans continue)
What is that...?
You don't know
what it is?
This cute, little guy
is called a mandrake.
It's an extremely rare plant
to come across out in the wild.
Finding it in a place like
this was really lucky for us!
If people hear the shriek
it makes when it's pulled
out of the ground,
it might cause them to die
from the shock of the noise.
Oh, thank you.
(Groaning continues)
Die from shock?
It's a highly
toxic plant,
but if you extract
all the poison,
it becomes a very
useful cure‐all.
Uhh...
Here you are,
my friend!
Ah!
Uhh...
Like I said earlier,
I wanted to give you a
present to show my gratitude
for all that you've done!
I... uh...
This mandrake is the
perfect present for you.
It's a symbol of our
newfound friendship
and what that represents.
(Writhing groans)
No thanks.
♪Closing song♪