[WILLEM]
Marry me.
I will make you happy, Chtholly.
[CHTHOLLY whimpers]
[laughs]
You're looking
particularly smug.
Smug, me?
I look smug?
I assume something good
must have happened?
Uh! Well, I guess so, yeah.
At least I think so.
You know, you're just
like an open book.
Hey, Rhan.
What do you think
finding happiness...
it's all about?
To begin with,
happiness means different
things to different people.
To some, it means having
food on their table.
To others, it means
books on their shelf.
Some believe that
doing one's very best
is what truly matters
in the long run.
And some are only content
if they can overcome
hurdles in their path.
Some take joy in witnessing
and nourishing
the happiness of others.
While some, sadly,
revel in others' sorrow.
[CHTHOLLY] I gotta say, I didn't
expect such a long response.
You're giving me a joy thesis.
That said, most creatures do not
realize this about themselves.
They do not know what,
in actuality,
will bring them happiness.
Yet, they still talk about their
desire to find happiness
as if they knew where to look.
One day, such people may learn
that they were
blessed all along,
but they will never realize
it when they're happy.
In my opinion,
to know the truth,
one must simply listen
to their own heart.
Make sense?
I hope that successfully
answered your question
and made you somewhat happy.
[CHTHOLLY]
Oh, god. Why?
Why is everything so awkward?
How did I pursue him like
I did up until yesterday?
[CHTHOLLY grumbles]
This is so hard!
[CHTHOLLY] Maybe I could
ask to kiss him again.
Would he accept this time?
Yeah, surely he would.
I mean, he did propose to me.
We're like a couple
now... Probably.
I'll give it a shot later.
Yeah, I'm gonna go for it.
I have a plan!
[gasps]
[CHTHOLLY]
What was that look about?
Oh, quit blushing!
You're embarrassing yourself!
[WILLEM]
So, listen.
[CHTHOLLY]
What is it?
About yesterday's, um,
well, you-know-what.
[CHTHOLLY]
Oh, yeah.
[WILLEM]
I, um...
I just want you to know I fully
intend to keep my promise.
I'll spend the rest of
my life making you happ--
[GRICK]
Oh! There you are!
Look left, you crazy kids!
It's okay, Willem.
I made a promise to
you, too. Remember?
I'll be with you forever.
[MALE WORKER 11A]
Hey Boss,
where do you want
me to put this?
[GRICK]
Oh, over there is fine.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
but I'm here now.
What is this?
[GRICK]
Supposedly, they're the forces
of the visitor Elq Hrqstn.
Elq Hrqstn?
[GRICK]
According to legend,
this world was once
home to gods.
But they attacked the humans
in a bid to wipe them out.
The one at the top
is Carminelake,
the middle one is Jadenail,
and the last one is, uh...
[WILLEM]
He's Eboncandle.
[GRICK]
Yeah, that's the one!
Ha, ha, ha!
Of course you'd know.
Of course.
After all, I did
personally fight him.
[BOTH]
Uh?
Come on, Willem you're
tryin' too hard.
You don't have to be
like that with us.
It's true.
I should have asked them what
happened with the war.
After we took each
other out, I mean.
Yeah, whatever you say, friend,
but for now, let me lead you
to your destination.
[GIRL 11A]
Hey! Look, Pops is here!
Sis, hurry! Pops has finally
made it back to us!
[WILLEM]
Can I say "I'm home" now?
Doesn't feel right anymore.
[CHTHOLLY groans]
[ELQ]
Ship sailing the starry sky.
Light in the palm of the hand.
Clay doll walking on all fours.
[CHTHOLLY]
Something feels weird.
It's like I'm being called.
[CHTHOLLY]
Underground?
What is it?
Everything okay there, missy?
[rumbling]
[WILLEM, GRICK gasping]
[MOGDAMAN screams]
What is that thing?!
[CREW MEMBER 11A]
It's a monster!
Yes, that much is fairly
obvious, you fool!
What I want to know is
what the-- Come back here!
Oh, no.
Why did you leave?
This is so terrifying.
[yelps]
[NEPHREN]
Timere?
[GRICK]
Son of a--
Looks like we fell pretty far.
Apparently, there's been a
massive cave below Gomag City,
but what is it for?
[gasps]
[WILLEM]
Chtholly...?
[gasps]
[WILLEM groans]
Willem, why are you...?
What were you thinking?!
You know your body can't
handle this kind of strain!
I'm fine, don't worry about it.
[GRICK]
Hey, you all right?
[WILLEM]
Think so.
[GRICK] I have a feeling we need
to get out of here, and fast.
Yeah, but how?
This looks to be the
underground ruins
where that idiotic officer
sent out a squad to scavenge.
You see all those markers
that lead down that way?
Hopefully, they'll
direct us to the exit.
Course, that's assuming the path
hasn't caved in somewhere.
Not long ago, I could've
just flown out.
There's no need to worry,
I promise to keep you safe.
Well, I'd rather be the one
keeping you safe.
I understand, but guardians
have the right
as well as the duty to guard
their charges, don't they?
Who are you calling your charge?
I thought I was your, uh,
you know, your um...
Oh, you know.
[GRICK]
Oh... What is that stench?
Oh, yep. Found it.
These soldiers are the
excavations squad, right?
Yeah, poor guys.
This was terrible.
These wounds are definitely
a timere's work.
You can tell because of
how savage they are.
That thing's hangin' around
nearby, we're in big trouble.
[WILLEM]
Timere.
One of the beasts that
destroyed the world.
If they were really
humans all along,
then the monster
that did this...
[CHTHOLLY]
Elq.
[GRICK]
Hm?
[CHTHOLLY]
Yes, yes.
You want me to go there?
--All right, then.
--[WILLEM] Chtholly?
--I'm on my way.
--What's wrong?
Hey! Chtholly!
[GRICK]
Missy! Oh, come on!
Do you know what she's doing?
Men, prepare to take
off immediately!
[CREW MEMBER 11B]
We can't, sir!
Shaft Three's been done in.
I am a veteran First-Grade
Technical Officer!
I can fix that in my sleep!
I'm telling you to be ready
to leave once I'm done!
Is that understood?!
[CREW MEMBER 11B]
Right! Yes, sir!
[NOPHT]
Hey! Welcome back!
[NEPHREN]
Same to you.
Where's Rhan?
She's keeping watch over there.
Can we call it a day now?
Haven't we taken out enough?
[NEPHREN] You really
believe that's possible?
No, I just want this
nightmare to end
before more people get hurt.
Won't be over for
a while, though.
Worried about Chtholly,
Grick, and that T.O...
I hope they get back
in one piece.
[PIG WORKER 11A]
Don't be stupid!
Leave that crap behind!
But I went to all the
trouble to find it!
We don't have time
for this nonsense,
our lives are far
more important!
[ARMADILLO WORKER11A]
I'm not saying they're not...
[NOPHT] "Our lives are far
more important," huh?
Wise words, I'd say.
Not that I actually
understand them.
[rumbling]
Get some rest.
I bet you're tired.
I'll take care of this.
Got a job to do.
Lives to guard, futures
to save, and all that.
Same old, same old,
but I love it!
[WILLEM]
Chtholly, wait!
[WILLEM panting]
Chtholly!
Please, stop.
What are you doing?
Willem, is that you?
Yes, it's me, but you need
to focus right now.
Don't lose sight of yourself!
Uh! Will ya look at that.
Amazing. I never thought
I'd get the chance to see
two of these within a
borgle's short lifespan.
Oh, ouch!
Poor thing's been
stabbed clean through.
[WILLEM]
Is that Seniorious's hex?
[GRICK]
Is who what?
[WILLEM] You know how
fairy tales have curses
that can turn people into
frogs and things like that?
This is the same idea.
A curse that can turn anyone,
god or immortal, into a corpse.
A world-altering
ability exclusive
to the holy sword Seniorious.
If it was used on her,
then there's no way
she was just an ordinary
little girl.
[GRICK]
Uh?
[WILLEM]
Chtholly?
Chtholly!
[GRICK]
We gotta go!
Grab a hold of
your girl and run!
[WILLEM]
I got it.
Listen to me, Chtholly,
we're leaving.
Please, try to stay
in control of yourself.
Hang on.
I won't let anything
happen to you.
Willem...
I'm here, right here.
I'll always be here with you!
I can't... I don't know...
[WILLEM]
Chtholly?
Talk to me. What is it?
[GRICK] This way! Willem hurry,
we're running out of time!
[WILLEM]
Chtholly?
Please, Chtholly, say something!
Chtholly!
[MOGDAMAN] Ah! Damn it, even
the pressure valves are blown!
What, they are?
Is the ship done for then?
[MOGDAMAN groans]
Hell, no!
I am not about to die here!
I want you to bring me
every last thing
I could use to repair
this bastard!
[WILLEM] I never managed
to bring happiness
to anyone in my entire life.
That's why I wanted...
wanted to make you girls...
All I wanted to do was
to make you happy.
But I just... I...
Why does everything always
have to end up like this?
[GRICK]
You okay, missy?
I just want to be
in there with them.
Of course you do.
I'm sure that would make
them feel a lot better.
[sighs] I'm sorry.
I wish I could've done more
than just bring her back.
It's all right.
This wasn't anyone's fault, so
there isn't anyone to blame.
We all knew the ice we were
walking on with her was thin.
[CHTHOLLY]
Where am I?
I'm doing this for one reason.
It's for my love.
For love?
[LILLIA groans]
For that reason alone,
I have come to slay a god.
And yes, I fully realize
I'm here on a fool's errand.
But I have no other choice.
This man, he's the walking
definition of stupid.
So I have to move on
these idiotic ideas
before he can think them
up for himself.
Because, Willem's a
complete and utter moron.
Time to say goodbye.
Rest in peace!
Uh?
[CHTHOLLY]
What was that?
Welcome back to me, Chtholly.
I do know you.
We've met before.
[ELQ laughs]
Do you wanna know something?
Because I have something
I want you to know!
Tell me.
[ELQ] A long, long time ago,
a race called "humanity"
was attempting to
destroy the world.
To prevent the destruction,
the Poteaus,
three gods who were
watching over the world,
decided to lead an army in order
to wipe out all of humanity.
Sadly, they failed.
A human brave
killed their master
before they could overpower
their enemy to save the world.
No one could stop
the humans now.
They turned into beasts and
obliterated everything.
[ELQ] I bet you're wondering
who their master was.
Her name was Elq Hrqstn!
She was the last
of the visitors,
and she died as a child.
You're Elq. That's your
name, isn't it?
[ELQ] Uh-huh, but it is also
the name of your soul.
[ELQ]
Fairies like you
are created from
the souls of children
who were too young to
realize they were dead.
Ever since the day Lillia
arrived and killed me,
I've been dreaming.
I dream of being like her,
I dream of being as brave
and as strong as her.
And I dream of putting
my life on the line
and fighting for
the people I love.
[CHTHOLLY]
Is that what I am?
[ELQ] Yes, that is what
all Leprechauns are.
[CHTHOLLY]
What will happen to me, then?
[ELQ]
You already know, do you not?
No dream is able
to last forever.
[CHTHOLLY] And dreams are
so quickly forgotten,
until nothing at all
remains of them?
[ELQ]
It's all right.
You made it back here
to me just in time.
Rhan!
Thank you. I'm so exhausted.
Would you like to switch out
with Nephren for a short time?
[NOPHT]
Nah, she's kinda preoccupied.
Besides, I figure we've
probably taken out
all the timere in
the area by now.
By the way, Nopht, how is
your body currently feeling?
Oh, it's super great for some
crazy reason, and what's more,
Desperatio's doing everything
exactly the way I want, too!
[RHANTOLK]
Same for me.
In which case, could what
we're experiencing somehow
be positive effects from that
rather dubious massage?
Oh...
[RHANTOLK]
Meaning, that man
wasn't simply touching us like
he did for perverted reasons.
Wow, talk about mean.
You really do hate
that guy, don't you?
I just don't accept
him as readily.
[laughs]
It appears that our break
time has been cut short.
[NOPHT]
No problem, here.
Given the shape I'm in today,
I could take on another
10 or 20, easily!
[RHANTOLK] How about a
hundred or two, instead?
[NOPHT laughs] I think that
might be a little too much.
[RHANTOLK]
Is that so?
Unfortunate.
[NOPHT]
Huh?
Get ready.
At this point, we must prepare
for the very worst.
[NOPHT]
Yep, certainly looks that way.
This whole thing is
the very worst.
In the end, I failed to do it.
You failed to do what?
Talk to her.
I wanted to communicate
with Chtholly again.
I'd have even settled
for a fight.
I was given yet another
chance, and I wasted it.
[RHANTOLK]
I see.
[MOGDAMAN]
All right.
Emergency repairs done!
Power up the circuits, now!
[WOLF SOLDIER 11B]
Roger that.
Powering up the circuits!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Ready and aim!
Fire!
[SOLDIERS groan]
[PIGEON]
Captain!
Stay back.
We are the only ones
who can kill these beasts.
[BUNNY]
B-But how?
Don't ask.
Know this battlefield is
ours and kill or be killed
applies to us. This fight
is no longer your fight.
Oh god.
You hurt yourself protecting us.
Are you all right?
[NEPHREN]
You need to go.
Run.
[NEPHREN] I won't be able to
hold them off much longer.
Go, now.
[CREW MEMBER 11C]
Three is too damaged
for it to stay on the grid!
Two and six are fine, though!
Reroute the load to them!
Oh, for cryin' out loud, I've
only ever flown small ships!
Can you give a guy a break?
[cannon fire]
[WILLEM]
Chtholly.
I don't...
I don't know what to say.
[WILLEM2]
You don't?
Maybe that's because
you never really cared
that much about her.
Remember how you couldn't
stop Lillia from fighting?
All you did was use
another wielder
of Seniorious as a substitute.
You couldn't keep your promise
to Almaria, either.
So you made a different promise
with this girl instead.
[WILLEM whimpers]
[WILLEM2] You never really saw
Chtholly for who she was,
and you always treated
her like a child.
That way you'd have an
excuse to discount her.
[WILLEM] You're wrong!
I wanted her to--
[WILLEM2]
You need to face it.
You lied to them.
[WILLEM whimpers]
[WILLEM]
I will make you happy, Chtholly.
I failed.
I fell short of my
promise... again.
[crash, glass shatters]
[WILLEM]
And now you.
Yet another beast?
Welcome, then, but you
should know, right now,
I need someone to take
some rage out on.
[ELQ] There's barely anything
"you" left of you.
Your mind and body have been
almost entirely replaced.
They've been replaced by
my body and mind, naturally.
I'm glad you made it here
before you disappeared
completely, though.
Your joys, and your sorrows,
oh, and your love for someone.
I know you must surely still
remember those things,
just a little bit?
You do, do you not?
Yes, but only a very little bit.
Yay! That must be a relief.
Everything's all right,
and you're still Chtholly!
[CHTHOLLY gasping]
Will... em...
[CHTHOLLY]
Final Episode: Chtholly.