[laughs]
I'm so glad you're here!
[GIRLS]
Welcome home!
[gasps] Chtholly?
[CHTHOLLY]
I'm back home.
Jerk.
[SOUWONG] You mean there's a man
here who can tune dug weapons?
No, no, no, no.
Sorry, it was not my
intention to frighten you.
I know this scary face
doesn't help.
However, it still seems like
you're telling me a tall tale.
I once knew a monster
that could tune dug weapons,
but he's long gone.
In there, huh?
[GIRL 06A]
Yes, Great Sage.
According to what I've been
told, he can tune dug weapons.
[SOUWONG] You've brought
him this far to meet me,
so we might as well
get on with it.
It's been a long time
since I've met a con man
with this much originality.
Hello? Souwong?
Really good to see you.
Wow, you look different.
In like a super old way.
No, that can't be
Black Agate Swordmaster?
No one's called me
that in a long time.
Magus of the Pole Star.
You look delighted to know
that we're both doing so well.
[SOUWONG] You spent 500 years
petrified on the surface?
I assumed you were dead
because my pulse tracing
never got any response.
None, ever!
Well, you wouldn't.
I was petrified,
so my heart wasn't beating.
[SOUWONG] Give me back
the tears I shed that day!
Ah, you mean you cried for me.
[SOUWONG]
No, I did not.
Don't be silly.
I would never waste my time
crying over someone like you.
Sure.
So, what's your deal?
Why are you still alive?
What's it been...
500 years, now?
[gasps] You...
What is that?
[SOUWONG]
You weren't the only one
killed during battle, you know.
I was taken out at
the same time as Emissa.
However, just before I passed,
I was able to place a curse
on myself, a curse that
would alter my life force.
What I am now can no longer
be considered human.
But that's mainly because I
can't die of injury or old age.
I see.
Don't get the wrong idea,
your pity isn't necessary.
I'm actually very happy with
the way my life has turned out.
[WILLEM]
No. It's not about your story.
I'm more shocked that Emissa
was killed in battle.
[SOUWONG sighs]
[WILLEM]
Look at 'em go.
Ya think that's Emissa?
Nah. It's most likely Hillgram.
Saw some gaping ridgelines
on the way here.
[sighs] Makes sense.
Will you look at this party?
It's practically
full of monsters.
[SOUWONG]
You're one to talk.
Huh, Black Agate Swordmaster?
How many times do
I have to tell you
to stop calling me
that, Souwong?
Also, you seriously need
to stop wearing that cape.
You look ridiculous.
[LILLIA laughs]
Now, that's not fair.
I mean, he's so itty-bitty,
how are we supposed to spot
him if he's not wearing it?
But it is ridiculous.
[WILLEM laughs] I guess that
means it really does suit
the great Magus of
the Pole Star.
Ah! You two are so good
at getting on my nerves!
Mm?
[WILLEM] Well then,
eat this and try to relax.
It's one of Almaria's
special ginger cookies.
Almaria baked
something for me?!
No, for me!
No, you're both wrong.
It's for...
--[SOUWONG yells]
--[WILLEN groans]
[crash]
[WILLEM groaning]
Good grief.
What am I gonna
do with you guys?
I haven't been able
to reminisce,
at least not before now.
Seems this job's helping
me deal with the past.
[gasps] Yes, of course!
That makes perfect sense!
You are the only one
who can tune carillons.
No one is more perfect for the
fairy warehouse caretaker job!
But now, I don't know if I
should leave you there to rot
or give you something
more fulfilling to do.
Not to interrupt your
brainstorm attack,
but you don't have to worry.
I'm perfectly fine.
And I swore to return soon,
so I need to get back.
Get back? To where?
Are you talking about
the fairy warehouse?
[WILLEM]
Yeah.
I'd love to stay and chat,
but I just can't right now.
It's nice to know we're
both still alive, though.
[SOUWONG]
No so fast.
Before you leave,
there's someone I'd
like for you to meet.
[WILLEM]
Uh?
[SOUWONG]
But I should warn you,
this is probably someone you
never imagined you'd see again.
[WILLEM]
You can't be serious.
You don't mean another one
of our friends survived?
We will be heading
for Island Two.
Ready an airship
for us immediately.
No, hang on a sec.
I never said I'd go!
Souwong! Wait!
[ELQ]
Room without an exit.
Black cat that doesn't
stop meowing.
Who's the unfamiliar
blue-eyed girl?
[gasps]
[bed creaks]
That was a weird dream.
Please come back, Willem.
Please.
[WILLEM]
Oh, no.
She's gonna be so mad at me.
[WILLEM]
Fun, feels like we're entering
the temple of an evil clan.
[SOUWONG]
I may have known you forever,
but I still don't get
your bizarre style.
[WILLEM laughs]
Look who's talking.
Five hundred years,
and you're still wearing
a ridiculous white cape.
[SOUWONG] Don't make
it sound like a disease.
It's a part of my
very heart and soul!
I would never cast my cape
aside, not in a thousand years!
[WILLEM]
Thank you.
[SOUWONG]
Where did that come from?
Why would you thank me?
Just felt like saying thank you.
Don't worry about it.
[SOUWONG]
No, no, wait. Why not?
What are you grinning for?
Don't be weird.
[rumbling]
[SOUWONG]
Out on a walk, are we?
Well, it is a pleasant day.
I'm meeting her?
Not her. Look lower.
[SOUWONG] Greetings, you
oversized piece of trash,
I've come to see you!
Uh! If it isn't the great Sage.
Wonderful timing. I was getting
unbelievably bored.
[WILLEM]
Mm...
[SOUWONG]
I've brought an old acquaintance
I'd like you to meet.
All right, Eboncandle?
Ah! Yes, of course,
I recognize you!
Yes, but where do I know you?
Oh! We fought...
Tell me, Souwong, please
tell me this isn't real
and it's all just a bad dream.
If you want, I don't
mind slapping you
so you can make
sure you're awake.
[WILLEM]
I think I'll pass.
[EBONCANDLE] It's been eons,
has it not, human brave?
[EBONCANDLE laughs]
[EBONCANDLE] I never
imagined the day would come
when our paths
would cross again.
Although I wish very much
that it were not so,
sadly, we are fated to always
cross swords, too.
Warriors like us are not
given such luxuries, uh.
Look, you can give all
that warrior crap a rest.
Really? How dreadfully boring.
Not to be rude, but why the
hell do you look like that?
The Eboncandle I fought in
the past had skin, flesh,
and you know, an actual
body from the neck down.
[EBONCANDLE] You ask
as if you weren't the one
who burned my
remains to a crisp!
Can you imagine my shock
when I awoke in this state?
This is your fault!
Although, it is not your fault
that I have had to consistently
use much of my power.
I've not had the strength
to heal myself completely.
I get it.
The "paradise" or
islands in the sky,
they were built by
the two of you.
That is correct.
In order to escape the seventeen
beasts, I used brute force
to elevate surface
land into the sky.
Somehow, it's managed
to last 500 years.
[EBONCANDLE] Eight-tenths of
it is thanks to my powers.
[EBONCANDLE laughs]
[WILLEM]
At this point, you have to know
what the seventeen
beasts are, right?
What the hell happened
to make them appear?
Where did they come from?
[EBONCANDLE] Hm... The beasts
are the true sin of humanity.
To begin with, they're ancient--
[SOUWONG] Do you remember
True World, by chance?
Uh. Now that you mention
it, yeah, I think I do.
Are you talking about that
really old, militant cult
we were ordered to take out?
[SOUWONG] Yes. The beasts
are biological weapons
that were born as a result of
True World's failed research.
[WILLEM]
Makes sense.
That's why emnetwihts are blamed
for destroying the surface.
It's because of them.
[SOUWONG]
Correct.
And they're not wrong.
Humans did destroy the surface.
But wouldn't you like to
take the surface back now?
[gasps]
[SOUWONG] You may be one
of the most annoying guys
I ever met. Rotten to the core,
I'm talking personality,
heart, and soul-all of it--.
But you also have the best
and most reliable skills.
Which means you're more than
worthy to be a part of our plan.
In fact, you're a crucial
factor at this point.
Indeed.
[WILLEM] I thought the
surface was overrun.
Isn't it a danger zone
with beasts everywhere?
What are you planning?
--We will attack them ourselves.
--What?
Now that you're here,
we also have the ability
to use carillons that couldn't
be tuned or wielded before,
giving us more power
than we'd expected.
This is significant
progress for us.
The battle will more than
likely require all resources
from every Règles Aile city.
It will be a long road.
Dangerous.
However, we stand a good chance
of coming out on top this time.
We can procure as
many fairies as we need.
The only problem previously
was the shortage of
usable carillons.
What?
I--! Uh. Nothing.
Uh, nothing at all.
Said too much again.
[CHTHOLLY]
We are the special weapons
you were sent here to care for.
[WILLEM]
It's you.
You're the ones who've been
producing the girls.
[PA ANNOUNCER 6A] Attention
operatives: move on the double!
Unknown beast detected.
Island Fifteen will
hereby be abandoned.
Strategic HQ is to fall
back to Island Sixteen.
[ELQ]
Hardcover picture book.
Black and white zigzag.
Swaying boat.
Damaged cocoon.
Red water. Ashen wind.
Seven-eyed frog.
Endless orange road.
Fabric with a silver glint.
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
Stop it, stop!
Who are you?! Shut up!
Shut up! Get out of my head!
Chtholly...
[MONSTER 6A roars]
[CHTHOLLY]
I promised.
I will go back.
I promised!
I promised. I promised him!
[WILLEM] These weapons use
the enemy's own force
against them as soon
as contact is made.
[ELQ]
Lion eating a snake.
Round rainbow.
Pile of gold coins.
Tiny bowl filled with sweets.
Burning signpost.
Fish flying between the stars.
Just shut up!
It doesn't matter what you say!
I'm going back!
I... I have to go back, to go...
Go back... to him.
[CHTHOLLY]
Go back to him.
[SOUWONG] Those fairies are
borderline unstable ghosts,
they're souls of children.
Souls who aren't aware
they're dead
when they wander into our world,
still trapped in the immaturity
of their former youth.
Remember, they're not
really life forms.
And one of my necromancy
skills allows me
to produce fairies from
wandering spirits like theirs.
[EBONCANDLE]
Since they do not fear death,
they make ideal,
mass-produced weapons
that can cause
venenum explosions.
[SOUWONG]
Their life-spans are very short.
And their spirits are so fragile
that if they generate too much
venenum during combat,
memories of their past
lives can come back,
causing mental disintegration.
But we're trying to
protect the world here,
these are simply sacrifices that
can and must be overlooked.
How are you girls feeling?
You three slept in
pretty late today.
We did, yeah.
Can you blame us?
That battle was rough.
[NEPHREN]
I think I'm dead.
We'd like to take it easy
for a while, if that's okay.
Right, Chtholly?
Chtholly?
Well, that's fine with me.
No need to push if you're
still so worn out.
[ITHEA] On that note,
you should excuse us
from chores for the time being.
[NYGGLATHO]
Not happening.
Sorry. I think I need
to go get some more sleep.
[ELQ]
Flat spider.
Used-up candles and
burned envelopes.
[CHTHOLLY]
Please stop...
--[ELQ] Half-eaten cookie.
--[CHTHOLLY] Please.
[ELQ] Metal bird and
rainbow-colored arrowhead.
Vivid mine.
Stomach with a thorn.
[CHTHOLLY]
Please, shut up.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
We made a promise...
What if I, what if I'm
the one who breaks it?
Aw. I was really looking forward
to eating all that butter cake.
[ELQ]
Threads made of morning dew.
Breaking world. Father.
Yellow plushie.
Shining skylark nest.
Pebble in a paper packet.
Carnival in water.
Black cat that doesn't
stop meowing.
Dazzling gray sky.
Kiss of a golden butterfly.
But who are you?
[ELQ]
Who are?
[CHTHOLLY, ELQ]
Who am?
[CHTHOLLY]
Who am... Who?
I don't know who I am.
The fairies are our only way
to make use of the carillons,
and this is a fact even
you cannot deny.
Yes, I realize they're
needed for basic defense.
But their lives shouldn't
be thrown away
to satisfy imperialistic urges!
What would you have me do?!
The world as we know it heads
steadily toward ruin.
Règles Aile's existence is
already on borrowed time
and borrowed power.
We have no choice, we must find
a way to return to the surface.
Must we? Are you sure
there's not a better way?
All those people living
out there, now,
they consider Règles
Aile their home!
Not the damn surface!
You know that!
What about you, do you consider
these islands your home?
Don't pretend like you
don't want to go back!
[WILLEM] Souwong, let's say
we do take the surface,
who are we gonna find there?
Will there be any of
our family or our friends
to welcome us home?
[SOUWONG]
Mm.
[EBONCANDLE] Great Sage,
I would give this fight up
for the moment, if I were you.
That is one resolute man.
Once he makes a decision
to protect something,
he will protect it, even if that
means sacrificing his own life.
[SOUWONG] You mean to tell me
you care more about fairies
who will soon die than
this world's future?
[WILLEM]
I do.
Now I need to go.
I promised to get back
to them quickly.
Then, Willem Kmetsch, I take
it this is your decision
on the matter today.
Yes, it is.
I always thought you
took the hero part
of heroic brave a
little too seriously.
So did I.
[BURONNY]
I've come with an urgent report.
It's about the wielder of
the dug weapon Seniorious.
Memories of her past
are returning.
Her mind has begun
to disintegrate.
[gasps]
[EBONCANDLE] And just like that,
he is gone.
Why did you not tell him
the truth about the beasts?
[SOUWONG]
I used to look up to him
like he was an older brother.
So if there's any way
I can help it,
I'd rather not make him hate me
more than he already does now.
[GIRL 2C]
No, it's mine!
[GIRL 2B]
Nuh uh, because I took it first!
Hey, do you guys know
where Nygglatho is?
[GIRLS]
She went up in the mountains!
Whenever someone doesn't
come back, she goes up
into to the mountains to
fight bears for a while.
Oh, right.
Then I guess we'll be
having stewed bear
for dinner tonight, huh?
[GIRLS whine]
Hey, what's wrong
with you, Tiat?
You seem gloomy.
Uh, I dunno.
It feels like there's
a big hole in my head.
[COLLON]
Why? Because Chtholly broke?
[TIAT]
Maybe, yeah.
[ITHEA] You should know
she kept her promise.
She wasn't supposed
to return from battle,
but because of you she
somehow made it home.
And she did everything
she could to make sure
she had a little
bit of time left.
[WILLEM]
Yeah.
I knew she'd keep her promise,
even though I wouldn't say
or do what she wanted.
[WILLEM]
I did nothing for her.
Chtholly!
[CHTHOLLY]
Are you looking for something?
[ELQ]
Uh-huh. Jade-ebo!
[CHTHOLLY]
"Jade-ebo"? I see.
Hey, who are you?
My name is Elq!
[CHTHOLLY]
Elq, huh?
I can help you find
Jade-ebo, if you want.
I don't mind looking with you.
I mean, this place seems huge.
Who, me?
Oh, yes, my name is... huh.
I think I forgot. Who am I?
Huh?
[CHTHOLLY]
I don't know,
but I remember there's
something important.
Oh, yeah. I remember
I have to go back.
[ELQ]
No matter what?
No matter what.
Even though it's only gonna
bring you bunches of pain?
Yes, even then, because I have
a promise I have to keep.
Okay.
[CHTHOLLY gasping]
[ELQ laughs]
[WILLEM]
It's rare to see you drinking
anything other than tea.
[NYGGLATHO]
I'm glad you're here, Willem.
I'm so tired of being
forced to cry all alone.
[WILLEM]
In the past,
I wanted to fix things
that couldn't be fixed,
like unhappiness or the
tragedies people went through.
But I was always too powerless.
In the end,
I couldn't do anything.
I started to wonder
why I even tried.
Still do.
You'd think I would've
learned my lesson.
[WILLEM] But I wanted
to make Chtholly happy.
I'll never understand it.
What did she ever see in me?
[CHTHOLLY] How do you not
know the answer to that?
[CHTHOLLY]
Just think about it.
You gave me so
many of my firsts.
At that market, you became
the first stranger to help me.
You were the first to take me
somewhere with a great view.
The first to inspire all these
different emotions in me.
You're the first person
who let me lean on them,
and the first
opponent I lost to.
There're so many,
I can't keep count.
Which is why, well,
it seems pretty obvious
that you'd be the first person
I ever fell in love with.
Take the hint already,
you dummy.
[cries]
What happened to me, anyway?
I remember getting
to the warehouse
and having a weird dream.
And then I was mad that
you wouldn't come back.
[CHTHOLLY] Why are you
looking at me like that?
[WILLEM]
Welcome home, Chtholly.
[WILLEM cries]
Welcome home.
[CHTHOLLY sobs]
It's a miracle of love.
I don't know about it being
love or not, but, yeah,
I'd say this is definitely
a miracle.
Knowing Chtholly, though,
she probably ignored
the consequences
and paid a huge price to make
whatever this is happen.
[CHTHOLLY]
Next Episode: home, sweet home.