[SOLDIER 12A grunting]
[SOLDIER 12A screams]
[WILLEM]
I feel like I must know you.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Forgive me.
Seems it's a bit too long.
I can't quite put a name
to your face anymore.
[WILLEM gasps]
[panting]
Tell me.
You wanted to fight them.
[WILLEM]
Yes, I did.
I believed that was the only
way I could help people.
I fought so I could protect
what was important.
The truth is, though,
I was being delusional.
I never protected anything.
I let it all slip
through my fingers.
What I'm doing now
doesn't actually matter.
Nothing is going to change.
How many times will I have to
suffer through this lesson?
[WILLEM]
All I know...
All I've ever really
known is to fight.
What am I doing here?
I wish I knew.
[WILLEM growls]
[MOGDAMAN] You! Stabilize
the ship, and do it now!
In case you haven't noticed,
I've got my hands full!
[MOGDAMAN]
Attention, everyone on board!
The bridge and power circuits
are top priority.
Defend them at all costs.
The ship will crash otherwise.
Grit your teeth
and fight, soldiers!
Yeah, that's easy
for you to say!
[SOLDIERS grunting]
[BIRDY gasping]
[CAT]
Oh, God!
[FROGGO]
Get off! No!
Thanks! Just in time!
[NEPHREN]
Stay back.
[BIRDY]
Wait. You sure you're okay?
[CAT]
We can fight with you!
[NEPHREN]
Do what I said.
Stay back.
This is what I'm here for.
[RHANTOLK grunts]
[RHANTOLK] Come on!
There's no end to them!
That said,
my sword is performing
better than it ever has.
I guess the T.O.'s skills must
be the real deal, after all.
My body's in incredible
shape, too.
Historia and I can do this.
Oh, no!
[RHANTOLK screams]
[RHANTOLK grunting]
[thud]
[RHANTOLK gasps]
Hey. You all right?
[RHANTOLK] What in the world
did you just do?
[WILLEM] Save you.
How's it look up there?
Nopht and Nephren?
Are they still fighting, too?
[gasps] I saw Nopht
not very long ago.
And, yes, as far as I know
she's still fighting.
Nephren, though, I haven't
seen in a while.
I can only assume she
must be in the hold
guarding the people
trapped there.
[RHANTOLK]
No.
How did you get
that kind of wound?
What have you been doing?
[WILLEM]
I've been... fighting.
Whether in the past, or now.
Fighting... is the only thing
I've ever been good for.
The only thing I've...
been good at.
[NOPHT yells]
[gasps]
[NOPHT grunts]
Not you, too.
Even you had to go and die.
I still don't get what you
meant by that line.
The "our lives are more
important" thing?
And if they are, why?
Wonder how the girls are doing.
Hope they're okay.
Got any idea how long
I've been out?
Oh, not terribly long.
A couple of minutes at most.
That's not too bad.
You shouldn't be
moving around like that.
Not with those injuries.
[WILLEM] Does this mean
you're worried about me?
I simply would prefer it if
you did not commit suicide.
Or use my friend as an excuse.
[WILLEM]
Understood. I'll try not to.
You're awfully strong,
aren't you?
Even unarmed, you can hold
your own against timere.
Suppose so.
Were all humans like you?
Was "ridiculously strong"
a common attribute?
It wasn't.
I was because...
I used to be a brave.
I was special, one of
the chosen warriors.
We took out enemies
to save people.
Being a brave was
a dream of mine.
So I trained in sword and
hand-to-hand combat.
I even learned how
to tune carillons.
I gained as much strength
as a person could
through sheer effort.
But it wasn't enough.
Whatever "strength"
I had was useless.
I couldn't save
who I cared about.
Not Almaria.
Not Lillia.
Not Chtholly.
Doubtful.
Winning in battle is not
the only way to save people.
[WILLEM]
Sit tight here.
Just for a little while.
Generating more venenum
now would be suicidal.
And you don't like that.
Say what you will.
You were a source of
salvation for Chtholly,
even if you can't see it.
[WILLEM gasping]
[CHTHOLLY]
Hey.
[ELQ]
What?
[CHTHOLLY]
I need a favor.
[gasps]
It'll be the last one.
No way!
Oh, please?
I think I made a promise to him.
It was a promise that he
wouldn't have to fight anymore.
And I... I would take on
the rest of his battles.
I would fight them for him.
No means no, and I said no!
I also need to
tell him something.
I have to go.
No matter what?
No matter what.
But, you'll disappear entirely
if you go back there again.
I don't mean just your memories.
Your most important
feelings will go!
All of it.
All of you will be gone forever!
I don't want to let that happen.
Sounds awful. But letting
things end this way?
To me, that would be
worse than anything.
Chtholly...
Please say yes.
Let me go.
One last time.
Let me go back to him.
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[NEPHREN panting]
[NEPHREN groans]
She's been hit!
Damn it!
[CAT]
...thing's gonna pay!
[BIRDY] Get the bastard!
Keep her safe at all costs!
--[FROGGO] I'll get this side!
--[CAT] I'm over here!
[NEPHREN gasping]
[BIRDY] Whoa! Watch out!
Here it comes again!
[NEPHREN]
Get back.
[BOTH gasp]
[NEPHREN gasping]
[FROGGO]
What's wrong?
[CAT]
We gotta help her!
[NOPHT]
Damn you. Get off!
Go away! Get off!
Get off, get off, get off!
Will you go away?!
We've regained control
of the main rotor.
[MOGDAMAN]
Good work, soldier!
[alarm blares]
[ARMADILLO]
We've lost altitude-control
wings three through five.
Seven is done for, too.
[MOGDAMAN]
What?! Agh, you!
You need to fix this!
Oh, fine. I will.
Now! Listen to me!
We're leaving this
area at top speed!
All hands, grab on to something
so you don't get thrown off!
[CAT, FROGGO yelp]
[SOLDIERS grunting]
[FROGGO]
It's our girl!
Hold tight.
Comin' to get you.
[NEPHREN]
Don't...
Please stay away.
It's too late.
The Gate's opening.
I... I...
I can't hold it off--
You just hang in there, missy!
And hurry up, toad, grab her!
[gasps] Ren!
[NEPHREN]
Willem?
Yes! It's me!
You're okay!
I think--
I think I maybe managed
to finally save someone.
[NEPHREN]
Huh...
[WILLEM]
Hold on.
I'll pull you up now.
[WILLEM groaning]
[WILLEM groans]
[NEPHREN]
Willem...
Please, don't say it.
[NEPHREN]
I generated too much venenum.
It's too late.
I'll figure something out!
[NEPHREN] The Gate will
probably open soon.
If it does,
this entire ship will blow.
I said I'll figure it out!
[WILLEM groaning]
[WILLEM panting]
[NEPHREN]
Willem, saving people is my job.
It's the job of all Leprechauns.
[WILLEM]
Ren, what are you--?
[NEPHREN]
It's all right.
Don't worry.
You've already saved us
plenty of times.
So please,
you have to let me go.
Don't say that.
Ren, I can't let you go.
[WILLEM gasps]
This isn't right.
I can't... Ren!
[NOPHT exhales, laughs]
[NOPHT]
Okay, this is real bad.
It's almost funny how
much I can't move now.
[clattering]
Hey. What are you--?
Don't be stupid!
If you can get up, then you need
to hurry and hide somewhere!
Chtholly!
What am I gonna do with him?
Please stop, Chtholly!
Come back!
We'll handle the fighting,
even your share.
You don't have to fight anymore,
so please, don't do it!
You're free to pursue
your happiness now.
So go grab it, and don't let go.
Be happy for us!
Otherwise, we'll never be able
to live with ourselves!
You're wrong.
I can't find happiness.
Meaning there's really no
reason for me to pursue it.
How can one pursue what
they already have?
Why would I try?
Don't you understand?
I'm the happiest girl
in the world.
[ELQ]
Books burning down.
Snake swimming in the flames.
Crumbling silver moon.
Princesses fighting
to the death.
Lies of the dead.
Big bell ringing.
Pillar of milk pouring...
Ribbon drifting in the sky.
Chtholly. Hang in there!
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[WILLEM]
I'll save her if it kills me.
[WILLEM grunts]
Chtholly...?
[WILLEM gasping]
[CHTHOLLY]
We swore never to part.
With our vow, came euphoria.
[WILLEM]
We swore to be together forever.
With our vow, came peace.
[CHTHOLLY]
My love for him was undeniable.
[WILLEM] What she meant
to me was undeniable.
[CHTHOLLY]
There was no greater happiness.
[WILLEM]
There was no greater joy.
[CHTHOLLY]
Yet, he offered more.
[WILLEM]
I promised to make her happy.
[CHTHOLLY]
And I delighted in it.
[WILLEM]
And I-- I was comforted.
[CHTHOLLY] The gifts of love
and bliss he presented to me
were unlike anything
I'd ever known.
[WILLEM] She granted me more
than I ever believed possible.
But I--
[CHTHOLLY] My life became his,
and his mine.
He blessed me with his world.
There is no joy ever known
that can compare with my own.
[footsteps]
[CHTHOLLY]
Will... em.
Thank you so much.
[WILLEM whimpers]
[WILLEM]
You goddamn fool.
[bell tolls]
[LIMESKIN]
I'll never get used to it.
No matter how often it happens,
losing warriors
never gets easier.
The struggle within your hearts
must have been
the most difficult.
There's no battle more
merciless and painful than that.
Well done on staying fighters
until the very end.
[NOPHT]
I've never been so angry!
I told that girl not
to fight anymore!
I said that it was our turn!
But no, of course not!
She just couldn't help
her stupid self! Damn!
Whatever, the happiest girl
in the world, my ass!
How could she possibly think
we'd be okay with
this situation?!
She goes out in
a blaze of glory,
and all's well that ends well?
There's nothing well
about any of this, okay?!
[RHANTOLK]
Nopht, please be quiet.
[NOPHT grunts]
[RHANTOLK] One's happiness
is one's own to define
and to decide. Looking down
on someone else's decision
or trying to make
that choice for them
is nothing more than oppression.
Well, then, pardon
my oppression-ness!
[NOPHT growls]
[RHANTOLK]
You know.
All things equal, if anyone
can bestow happiness,
it's people like you.
People who will always
stay true to the good
within their oppressive natures.
It looks like spring is coming.
[BOTH panting]
[TIAT]
Five more laps!
[COLLON]
Hard work and spirit!
Well, they're certainly
full of energy.
Yeah, you can say that again.
[TIAT, COLLON grunting]
Apparently, the girls
are working hard today.
They sure are.
Although, kinda sad their
favorite older fairies
aren't here to help 'em.
They might be getting
a little too worked up.
This does take me back.
Chtholly was just
like that, too.
She lost her older sister
figure like they did.
And she also used her sorrow
and loss as motivation
to grow even more powerful.
Ah, the joys of youth.
I don't know. I don't think
I could ever do that.
[ITHEA cries]
[ITHEA] I'm sorry,
could you maybe pretend
you didn't see this?
It's not the best
example to set.
You know, as the eldest.
[ITHEA cries]
See what? I don't know what
you're talking about.
[ITHEA whimpers]
[wails]
[SOUWONG]
No response at all?
My pulse tracing is sure
to locate anyone,
so long as they're
alive, that is.
Come on, now.
Black Agate Swordmaster.
[GIRL] Excuse the interruption,
Great Sage.
[SOUWONG]
Of course, that's it!
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
frighten you again.
Please forgive me!
[BABY cries]
[FAIRY 12A]
Listen to that!
Poor thing hasn't
let go of her feelings
from her past life yet.
She must have a
really pure heart.
[FAIRY 12B] By that, do you
mean simple and naïve?
[FAIRY 12A]
That is one way to look at it.
Good evening, sweetheart.
It's so nice to meet you.
[laughs] So stubborn.
Ugh. Here, let me try something.
There we go.
[muffled]
See? She got tired
and is now silent.
[FAIRY 12A]
That's enough of that...
[FAIRY 12A sighs]
Welcome, little one.
Welcome to this fragile,
dying world
with no redeeming
qualities whatsoever.
We're happy to have you.
[gasps]