[ELQ]
Solitude in white darkness.
Prayer echoing across
a cramped room.
It gets worse every day.
What am I gonna do?
[footsteps]
[gasps]
Oh, it's just you.
[ITHEA]
That's right!
Ithea Myse Valgulious here!
[ITHEA] Now. Mind telling me
exactly who you are?
[CHTHOLLY]
Who am I?
What do you mean?
[ITHEA] I want you to
tell me who you are.
Spell it out for me.
My name is Chtholly
Nota Seniorious.
I didn't need to worry!
You're definitely still
my friend Chtholly.
Worry, about what?
I don't understand.
Why would you worry?
[ITHEA] Look, you need to ignore
all those nonsensical visions,
words, and memories
of that past life.
Otherwise, they're gonna
just eat away at you
until you start losing
your own memories,
and I really don't want it to
make you forget who you are.
So all these memories,
they're true, they're real?
A girl with red hair
keeps telling me that.
[ITHEA]
Do not think about her anymore!
She doesn't matter.
That girl has nothing
to do with you.
She's a total stranger,
and of no relation.
I want you to think
about who you are,
like as much as you can.
Cling to every memory
you still have now.
Don't let them be swept
away by someone else's.
[CHTHOLLY gasping]
And no generating
venenum anymore.
Jeez, what were you thinking?
But, I had to help her, I--
No "buts" allowed, Chtholly.
Yes, you were very
lucky one time.
You came back!
But, who knows what might
happen next time, though.
Avoid anything that might
trigger a memory of a past life,
and do not generate venenum.
If you wanna stick around
for as long as possible,
you need to follow
these two rules!
I knew it.
My stupid disintegration never
actually stopped, did it?
So, you still decided
to live on, yeah?
Listen. I've got a
story for ya, okay?
It's about a girl I once knew.
We were really close.
Just like you, the girl's
past life slowly but surely
ate away at her until
her own persona vanished.
Meanwhile, the other girl
who woke up in her place
felt pretty lost, herself.
She'd thought she'd died,
but here she was in a place
she'd never been before,
and in a body that wasn't hers.
[ITHEA] Lucky for her,
she came across a diary
that belonged to the girl who'd
completely disappeared.
She'd written in it every
single day without fail.
Ithea?
She was a bubbly, nosey girl.
I think she focused
on everyone else
so she wouldn't have
to reveal her feelings.
Yep, that's the kind of girl
Ithea Myse Valgulious was.
When it happened,
I thought perhaps killing
myself was for the best.
But then, we'd both be gone.
It would mean nothing.
I realized there was only
one way for me to atone.
I'd stay.
I'd have to take over
being Ithea,
and I'd never, ever let anyone
know I wasn't really her.
Funny, somehow I've made
it all the way to today
just by saying that to
myself over and over.
I see.
I'm so sorry.
She had a diary.
Maybe I should start one, too.
Try asking yourself this, first.
Do you want someone
to take over your life?
How does the Chtholly here,
the you right now, how does
she want to live? Hm?
The me here.
The me now.
Uh.
It's getting kinda chilly out.
I'll help. I'm not as
warm as Nephren,
but I'll do my best
to keep you comfy.
You're just gonna
have to make do.
Thank you, but y'know,
you actually seem
pretty warm to me.
It makes me happy to hear that.
Chtholly.
You think you can keep
this from the T.O?
[CHTHOLLY]
Yeah.
Besides, knowing would only
make him worry even more.
And I refuse to be the
damsel in distress type.
That's it.
I know what I want to do.
Right now, I just want to savor
the joy of being with him.
I want to revel in being normal.
See, there's that whole "look at
me, I'm in love" thing you do.
Told ya. I knew you
were definitely still
good ol' Chtholly!
Oh, stop.
[ITHEA]
You're the only one.
About Ithea and the diary.
You're the only one I've told.
[CHTHOLLY] Then,
it can be our little secret.
Are you gonna ask me?
Like, don't you wanna
know my real name?
Or find out what kind
of person I was before?
You're Ithea, too, though.
A bubbly, nosey girl.
One who focuses on
everyone else so she doesn't
have to reveal her feelings.
She's a fellow fairy,
and one of my best friends.
That's all that really matters.
It is. Thank you.
That's such a relief.
Let's go!
[footsteps]
[CHTHOLLY yells]
[GIRLS]
Mm?
[door creaks]
Oh, was that just you, Chtholly?
I'm sorry.
Was I being too loud?
[gasps] Your hair
is still changing.
Yeah. I'm really
starting to like it.
Yes, I can tell.
I mean, you're owning it!
Thank you!
[CHTHOLLY yells]
[CHTHOLLY]
I'm done being all mopey.
[GIRLS gasping]
[CHTHOLLY]
But even when I'm sad,
even when I feel like
I'm being torn apart,
even the tears that are
always ready to flow,
they all prove I'm still here.
All the worry, the frustration,
the sorrow, and the joy.
They're all different parts
of what make up the person
standing right here,
the person alive right now.
The girl who is, without
a doubt, me... Chtholly.
[CHTHOLLY]
Yes, at least for now.
[gasps]
[NEPHREN]
You're knitting?
It's gotten pretty cold lately.
The little ones don't have
anything warm enough to wear,
so I thought I'd help.
That's nice.
So, whatcha say?
Some people think this
color suits me, do you?
Okay, what's the matter?
You don't have to worry.
All right, then. If you say so.
[CHTHOLLY]
Thank you, Ren.
[sneezes]
[gasping]
[WILLEM]
How's Collon's cold?
Is she gonna be okay?
[NYGGLATHO] Still not over
the hump yet, I'd say.
I'm gonna pick her up
some medicine later.
[WILLEM]
Sounds good.
Oh, yes, this is great!
You're improving so much!
Chtholly. When you
get a chance,
will you put this under
Collon's pillow for me?
It's an ancient talisman
to prevent nightmares
when you have a cold.
[gasps]
[WILLEM] Is that okay?
I'm worried about her.
Her cold has lasted so long.
[CHTHOLLY]
Oh, right. That's fine.
Collon. Got it.
[WILLEM]
Uh.
How neat! I didn't know you
had something like this.
Not me. Seniorious provided it.
[NYGGLATHO]
Did you say Seniorious?
[WILLEM] Yeah, I told you that
dug weapons were comprised
of several different
talismans, didn't I?
Uh...
[WILLEM]
The other ones prevent cuts
when the blade isn't
imbued with magic,
or they raise an alarm when
the wielder uses an alias.
They're kinda useless
at the moment,
so I figured we might--
You put that talisman
back right now!
What has gotten into you?!
Do I have to remind you
that dug weapons aren't
every day little charms that
we can hand out willy-nilly
for whatever we want
whenever we want it.
They're ultimate weapons,
ones that should be prioritized
better than this!
[WILLEM laughs] You're being
overdramatic, and you know it.
Unless you think
Collon's not a priority,
and that she doesn't need
a good night's sleep.
[sighs]
[NYGGLATHO]
What am I gonna do with you?
Oh, fine. Of course, I'm
worried about her, too.
Just promise me
you'll put it back
before you go to the surface.
I promise.
Speaking of the surface, do you
think they're okay down there?
What were their names again?
Nopht and Rhantolk, right?
[NYGGLATHO] Yes, and there's
currently no need
to be troubled.
For what it's worth,
the military is rushing to
finish the ship's remodeling.
Well, that's reassuring to hear.
I'm concerned about that
artifact they recovered, too.
[NYGGLATHO]
Oh, that's right.
Lapidemsibilus.
You're worried about it
'cause you worry about me
which you do too much.
He's an overprotective
daddy, this one.
[WILLEM]
Uh. Shut up.
[NYGGLATHO]
What? It's better
than being an
overprotective sugar daddy!
[WILLEM]
Oh, come on. Not you, too.
You both should shut up.
Neither of you are making sense.
[CHTHOLLY]
Uh... Here we go.
[WILLEM]
Huh...
[CHTHOLLY]
What?
[WILLEM] You've been doing
more stuff like that lately.
It gives you that traditional,
girly girl charm.
[CHTHOLLY gasps] I have
to count the stitches,
so I'd appreciate it if
you didn't distract me!
[WILLEM] What? I was just
trying to compliment you.
[CHTHOLLY]
That was a compliment?!
[yawns] You're still up, Rhan?
--Wow.
--Yes.
I wonder how long this
rescue squad is gonna take,
it's been like forever.
I just got the word.
It's gonna take them
even longer to get ready.
[NOPHT] You're trying
to read that again?
I am.
[NOPHT]
Figure anything out?
I haven't.
But I believe I can come up with
an alternative interpretation
for this passage.
Humans by the surface.
No...
By the humans, the surface...
The surface's...? [gasps]
Nopht, will you kindly and
immediately get off me.
[knocking]
[WILLEM]
It's open.
[door creaks]
[door slams]
Staying up late again?
[WILLEM]
I guess, kinda.
[CHTHOLLY]
Um, so uh.
You know all those
things that you do?
[WILLEM]
Hm?
All those things that you do.
Can you teach me how
to do them, too?
Like how to tune the swords, and
that weird thing you did for me.
Y'know, the thing you
did with your hands.
Why are you looking
at me like that?!
[WILLEM sighs]
What's gotten into you?
Lately, you haven't
given me much attention,
probably because you
didn't have a reason to.
I thought you'd make time
for me if I was learning,
and any time spent
together works for me.
[WILLEM]
You can't be serious.
Although I can't fight,
I'm still forcing you to take
me to the surface with you,
so I would like to be useful.
None of those skills
are something
you can master overnight.
You would have to put in a lot
of time and effort first.
[CHTHOLLY]
Mm.
Don't get too worked up.
I know how you feel,
but I'm still not going to
make you push yourself.
Don't be silly.
I wouldn't push myself.
[WILLEM]
And don't you play dumb.
You've been losing your
memories, haven't you?
[gasps] I didn't realize
that you knew.
[WILLEM]
I could tell from watching you.
So you were watching me.
But, if we have Lapidemsibilus,
we won't have to
worry about that.
[CHTHOLLY]
Is that map of the surface?
[WILLEM] Yep, it's the
area near the ruins,
where the survey
team was attacked.
[CHTHOLLY] Isn't this
where the rescue squad
is supposed to land?
That's a bit close to camp,
don't you think?
Oh, but I suppose that
would make it easier
to transfer the haul.
[WILLEM] Well, aren't you
quick on the uptake?
I am your secretary, after all!
Where we're going is
your home, isn't it?
Five hundred years ago.
[CHTHOLLY]
Would you want to go back?
This island has become
my home now.
Our home.
It is. Yes.
Hey. What was your city like?
Did it have really amazing food?
Were you in love there?
[WILLEM] What's all this,
why the sudden interrogation?
It's my understanding that
one needs detailed intel
on their destination beforehand.
But wait!
I'm gonna go get
some more tea, first.
Be right back.
Give me a break,
you're just curious.
This is so good.
[CHTHOLLY] Rather than
worry and be stagnant,
I'll keep moving forward,
one step at a time.
My footsteps may fade behind me,
and the path ahead may
be dark as well.
But, I won't regret the past,
or be pessimistic
about the future.
[CHTHOLLY] I will simply live
here in the moment.
Because no matter
how I fight it,
the clock keeps
ticking down on me.
[CHTHOLLY]
11... 12... 13... 14...
Perfect! [laughs]
[ALMITA]
Auntie Nee!
[NYGGLATHO laughs]
[CHTHOLLY] And time,
it keeps on passing by.
[GIRLS laughing]
[CHTHOLLY]
I'm glad I finished in time.
Uh, this is for Tiat.
[TIAT]
Me? Really?
Thank you so much!
I'll love it forever!
[ALMITA gasping]
[CHTHOLLY]
This one is for... Lakhesh!
Wow, um, thank you
very much, Chtholly!
[COLLON]
What about Collon?
Hey, what about me,
where's mine?
[PANNIBAL]
Collon needs to wait her turn.
[CHTHOLLY]
Here you go, sweetie.
[gasping] Oh, it's so warm!
[ITHEA]
The rest of you better hurry
and get your butts
over here, too.
Chtholly's giving out presents!
[GIRLS cheer]
All right, so what's
the deal with this party?
It's a snowfall fest.
It's for snowy nights,
when you can't go out.
Instead, you wine
and dine all night long.
[WILLEM]
Huh.
[NYGGLATHO]
It's a popular event these days,
but originally, it was one
of our troll festivals.
[WILLEM] Uh... I think
I'll pass on the details.
But, let's say
it's also a send-off
for those of you headed
to the surface.
It's really not that
big a deal, is it?
Um, so we have presents
for the older fairies, too.
Although, I guess they
aren't exactly from us.
[NYGGLATHO gasping]
Gosh, you look so lovely,
I could eat you up right now!
Let go! You're squeezing
me too tight!
I can't breathe, and you're
gonna wrinkle my dress!
[ITHEA] Mm! I'm telling ya, that
there is one high-class lady.
I tip my hat to Lady
Phyra's good taste.
Why would she send us all this?
It's for the snowfall
fest, apparently.
[WILLEM]
Oh, um.
"Thank you all for your help
when you were here last.
I know this isn't much,
but I wanted to send some
gifts for the snowfall fest.
I hope you all come to visit me
in Corna di Luce again soon!"
What is it, Ren?
There is something for you.
[ITHEA muffled laughter]
Cheer up.
I can't believe that little--
[GIRLS gasping]
[TIAT]
Gorgeous!
[WILLEM gasps]
Look at that.
Get over there.
If there's ever been a
time to compliment her,
this is that time.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
I know what to say.
[ITHEA]
Say everything you want.
Ask everything you need.
Putting it off can be
a bad idea,
and you know that
better than anyone.
[GIRLS chattering]
[footsteps]
[WILLEM]
Hey, Chtholly.
Uh?
You look absolutely beautiful.
[GIRLS chattering]
I...
I know!
[CHTHOLLY]
This should be enough clothes.
What about books, though?
[knocking]
[NEPHREN] Chtholly,
it's almost time to leave.
[CHTHOLLY]
Oh, okay.
Who am I, really?
[GIRLS crying]
See you later.
We're off, girls.
[CHTHOLLY]
I can't stop it.
My memories are slowly fading.
The person I am
is crumbling away.
You girls better be good
for Nygglatho, okay?
[NYGGLATHO]
Be safe.
We'll prepare a "welcome back"
party for you while we wait.
[ITHEA grunts]
[ITHEA]
Don't push yourself.
It's a promise, right?
[CHTHOLLY]
It's a promise.
[GIRLS cry]
[CHTHOLLY]
I'm...
I'm so sorry.
[CHTHOLLY]
It's sad.
I've forgotten more than half
of what I knew about them.
I can relearn the names I can't
remember anymore, however,
I know the memories I've
lost will never come back.
[CHTHOLLY]
As everything I am falls apart,
can I even be called
Chtholly at this point?
It's heartbreaking.
I'm hurt and just so sad.
[CHTHOLLY] But right now, I want
to hold all these feelings
as close to my heart as I can.
Because the moment
they disappear, too...
...that's the moment there
will be nothing left of me.
[NOPHT laughs]
Ren!
[NOPHT]
Heh! I never expected you
to be a part of
the rescue squad!
I swear, you're just as
teeny-tiny as ever!
[NOPHT]
Hey, since you're here,
that must mean the
massive timere
you guys were fighting ended
up being taken out, huh?
Which then means Chtholly
opened the Fairy Gate.
Um.
I guess that's, uh...
[NOPHT] You know, Chtholly and
I never got along that well.
But now.
I feel like I should have tried
harder--talked to her more.
[CHTHOLLY]
Um...
[NOPHT]
Don't "um" me.
I need to grieve for Chtholly.
So, long time no see, Nopht.
[NOPHT]
You!
Eh?
[NOPHT whimpers]
--It's a ghost!
--Hey, wait up!
You don't understand,
I'm still alive!
[NOPHT, CHTHOLLY chattering]
Well, that's a
good way to start.
[CHTHOLLY]
Next episode: my happiness.