[CHTHOLLY humming]
[NYGGLATHO] We've received
a message for you.
You've officially
been ordered to report
to the base on Island Forty-Nine
at noon tomorrow.
[WILLEM]
About the surface thing?
[NYGGLATHO] Makes me wonder
if they plan on using
one of our girls to help
with the rescue effort.
[WILLEM]
Not exactly excited.
Oh, no, forgot the pepper.
Okay. Which is pepper?
[SOLDIER 8A]
Get a move on!
[SOLDIER 8C]
Need medicine here!
[GRICK] We've sent word to
the Guardian Wings Military.
Just gotta take it easy.
Help should arrive fairly soon.
Yeah, that's a lot
easier said than done.
[GRICK]
It'll be fine.
Legitimitates, or the Fourths.
Won't run into them for a while.
Here!
And why do you think that?
I think that because I
know they tend to avoid
living close to their own kind.
There shouldn't be any
of 'em around here now.
Huh, had no clue.
Rhan, did you know about that?
[RHANTOLK]
Humans unleash the beasts,
and fill the world with...
They fill it with ashen truth.
[NOPHT]
Seriously, Rhan!
Your bad habit is showing!
What does Nygglatho
always tell you?
When it comes time to eat,
you need to focus on food!
Eat up already!
Open your mouth wider!
They really are just a couple
of children, aren't they?
Willem was right on the money.
[MOGDAMAN] We want to send a
rescue squad to the surface.
But the Plantaginesta, the
Moby-class transport airship
we would use, is currently
being remodeled.
It won't be ready for 15 days.
What the heck do
you need to have
such a big ship for, anyway?
[MOGDAMAN]
What?
[MOGDAMAN] Watch your mouth,
Second-Grade Technical Officer!
I'm a First-Grade Technical
Officer, you know!
I'm your superior!
Pardon me, First-Grade
Technical Officer, sir!
Please excuse this country
boy's lack of manners.
Forgiven. I may be a
first-grade technical officer,
but I still have
some compassion.
Now, let's get back on topic.
The survey team on the Saxifraga
was commissioned to excavate
specific ruins of
the emnetwihts.
They were rather successful and
retrieved numerous relics,
so we need a big ship to
bring everything back.
Understand, Second-Grade
Technical Officer?
Yeah-huh.
[MOGDAMAN grunting]
Understood, First-Grade
Technical Officer, sir!
But the longer the
rescue op is delayed,
the more danger the
survey team faces.
We know, that's why we
sent two swords with them
in the first place.
And I hope they do their jobs,
even if they must sacrifice
their own lives.
[clattering]
Huh?
Is there anything wrong?
No, not at all.
You're absolutely correct,
oh wise First-Grade
Technical Officer, sir.
[clears throat]
I can't read a disfeatured's
facial expressions.
Here.
I want you to go through this.
[WILLEM]
"Ground Level K96-MAL Ruins.
The second Survey Report."
[MOGDAMAN]
Once you read it,
you'll be able to appreciate
the importance of this survey.
[WILLEM]
Hang on.
Streets with thick stone paving.
Jerry-built housing blocks...
No doubt about it, this is Gomag
City, in Imperial territory.
It's... It's my hometown.
[MOGDAMAN]
On the next page,
you'll find a list
of their findings.
You know, talismans
and the like.
Those objects are precious
and informative.
They're awaiting our rescue.
[WILLEM gasps]
[WILLEM]
"Dug weapon Lapidemsibilus"?
This is it!
This sword can...
[WILLEM] Sir kind First-Grade
Technical Officer, sir?
What is it, Second-Grade
Technical Officer?
A favor. I would like
to ask one.
[laughs] Well,
that took forever.
Sorry. It's kind
of a long story.
Give me a second.
I just need to finish this.
There's no need to rush.
[CHTHOLLY]
That was delicious.
You ready?
Why did you come
with me again?
I wanted to buy myself
something, silly.
I also have a huge list of
things from the girls.
Well, you seem to be
enjoying yourself.
It isn't often you and I
can take a leisurely stroll
all by ourselves.
In fact, I don't think
that's ever happened.
What about when we first met?
We ran all over
the place that day.
[gasps]
Uh?
Um, that's true, but it
didn't like, you know...
It didn't have the
same feel back then.
Ready to go?
Chtholly...?
[inaudible]
[FROG BAKER 8A] Oh! Is that
a cute missus I see?
A "missus"?
Newlyweds, huh?
I'll give you a discount.
No, you've got this all wrong--
Yes! We are,
thank you very much!
Huh?!
[CHTHOLLY laughs]
[bell tolls]
[WILLEM] Are you finished
shopping now, "missus"?
Yep, and thank you
for all your help.
Newlyweds, huh?
So we look like a couple.
Are you really happy
right here?
You're finally free to
roam outside the island
practically anywhere you want,
so why come with
me just to shop?
Oh, come on.
Quit playing dumb when I
know you know the answer.
[WILLEM]
Mm?
You see, I don't care
where we are.
I just want...
I mean, all I want
is to be with you.
[sighs] I honestly have
no clue what you see in me.
[BOTH laugh]
[WILLEM] I was ordered to send
a fairy soldier to the surface.
[CHTHOLLY]
Yeah?
[WILLEM]
I picked Nephren.
And I'll be going with her.
[CHTHOLLY]
Right.
[WILLEM]
I don't think I can sit around
and wait for someone
to return anymore.
Also, I'm interested in a sword
they found on the surface.
A sword?
[WILLEM]
It's called Lapidemsibilus.
I believe it has
a special ability
to keep its wielder in
optimum mental condition.
[CHTHOLLY]
Mm.
So listen. I know you're
putting on a brave face.
The disintegration might
worsen at any moment.
My hope is that
this sword could help.
If it ever came down to it.
You're worried about me, then?
Did you really think
I would not be?
[CHTHOLLY] I don't think there's
any reason to worry.
Nothing has happened
since that one time.
I even sparred for a while
with Tiat the other day,
and I was fine afterward.
I feel great, so don't
worry so much.
You realize you're not
a leprechaun anymore?
[gasps]
So there's no telling
what's happening
inside your body right now.
I'm begging you,
please don't push yourself.
So then, when are you
supposed to be leaving?
Oh, not for a while yet.
You'll look after the girls?
[CHTHOLLY]
I'm going, too.
[WILLEM]
Huh?
I said I'm going with you.
Did I not just literally
beg you not to push yourself?
Yes, you did!
But I won't sit around
waiting for you to return.
--I don't think I could bear it.
--Absolutely not.
That excuse isn't
gonna fly with me.
You are not a fairy anymore,
and there's no sightseeing.
You think I'd want
to go with you
just to do some sightseeing?!
Wait. No, that's not what
I'm saying at all.
What I mean is, it's not
a place to go for fun.
You think this is all about fun?
Now, you've made me mad!
Now, I'm going with you,
no matter what!
Calm down.
You know that's not
gonna happen!
[CHTHOLLY] Looks like it's
gonna happen, after all!
Yay for permission!
Yeah, if you say so.
Hold on, are you mad at me?
Don't you realize why you
got permission to go?
Let's see, isn't it because
you vouched for me?
[WILLEM]
Sort of, I guess?
To be blunt, he thought
you were my lover.
Your lover...?
[CHTHOLLY laughs]
[MOGDAMAN grunting]
[WILLEM] Apparently, officers
often take lovers on trips
as their secretaries.
That is what he thinks
I'm doing.
Ha!
Your lover. [laughs]
I'm okay with that!
Well, that's great, but I'm not.
All right.
Then we can go back to "missus."
Oh, for pity's sake.
Look, truth be told,
I would rather not be separated
from you, either, okay?
[gasps] Wait a second!
I'm happy, but also sad because
it wasn't a proposal, was it?
[WILLEM]
Of course not.
[CHTHOLLY hums]
"I would rather not be
separated from you, either."
Oh, no, I totally
forgot the pepper!
It's second from the right,
window side.
[CHTHOLLY]
Pepper!
[door opens]
[footsteps]
[ITHEA]
T.O.
Hey, T.O.
Is that Ithea?
You betcha.
Your beloved Ithea
Myse Valgulious.
If you want anything
for breakfast,
best to hit the mess hall soon.
Yeah, okay. I'm up. I'm up.
[crash]
Owie.
You were being my
blanket, Ren?
That's why I felt
so warm. Thanks.
[NEPHREN]
You're welcome.
It gets chilly this
time of year,
and I didn't want you
to catch a cold.
[ITHEA]
When you think about it,
shouldn't this scenario be
ridiculously scandalous?
Why doesn't it seem
that way, though?
That's because your mind
hasn't been corrupted
by what they call
"the gutter" as of yet.
Not to mention Nephren
basically has pet status.
Are you okay with that?
Providing emotional
support is crucial.
It's a worthwhile role.
[ITHEA]
Is that so?
Anyway, what were you
researching all night?
It was a dug weapon,
Lapidemsibilus.
That sword could stop Chtholly's
mental disintegration.
[gasps]
[laughs]
Jeez, what now?
Nothing, just wondering if she
has a real chance with you.
Does she?
Don't be ludicrous, she had
a chance this entire time.
Some may hold out longer,
but no man can remain
unfazed forever when
a cute girl likes him.
But I still can't give in,
which is why I'm trying
to keep her at arm's length.
Wow.
You tell her, I'll end you.
[crash]
[CHTHOLLY]
You slept with Nephren?!
Why does everyone have
to make it a big deal?
You know Nephren is just
like a daughter to me.
Why are you being
so weird about it?
Spare me. You're not that
much older than she is!
[WILLEM] Yeah, well, people
tend to assume I'm young,
but I'm actually
over 500 years old.
True, and I imagine Nephren
must have snuggled up
in there with you herself.
No need to imagine.
But I still have a hard
time accepting this!
I know you can sense people
sneaking up on you!
I can only sense the
hostile people, though.
I don't notice the mostly
harmless ones.
Then let me ask you this.
What if the person crawling
in your bed was Nygglatho?
Defenestrated in
two seconds flat.
That's not how it
went with Nephren.
Nygglatho might not
technically be hostile,
but she is what I consider
a dangerous woman,
a very dangerous woman.
[CHTHOLLY]
M'kay.
What if it were me?
[WILLEM]
Uh. I don't know, let me think.
I'd have to throw
you out, obviously.
[CHTHOLLY grunts]
--[crash]
--[gasps]
Please be more
careful in the future.
You don't want the little ones
to start jumping in your bed.
At least I assume you don't.
Right. No.
[NYGGLATHO]
I give up.
I have no idea why Chtholly
isn't a leprechaun now,
or why her hair changed color.
What about you?
Will the dug weapon on the
surface really come in handy?
Willem?
[WILLEM gasps]
Oh, sorry.
It's just...
Chtholly was acting...
I dunno, kinda weird
this morning.
Huh?
[CHTHOLLY humming]
[WILLEM] So I said I'd
throw her out, obviously.
I thought she'd be mad over why
it's okay with Ren and not her,
but she just walked away.
You think she's sick again?
[NYGGLATHO laughs]
Y'know, for such
a perceptive guy,
you can be unbelievably obtuse.
[WILLEM]
What's that supposed to mean?
She's not sick,
she's just elated
that you put her in the same
category as you put me.
And that would make her
elated because why?
[NYGGLATHO]
Because I'm the rival in love
she's most worried about.
And if you treat both of us
the same, that would mean
you also see her as more
than just a little girl.
Hold on. Her rival in love?
Yes.
Are you saying she believes
you and I could get together,
like in a relationship?
[NYGGLATHO]
That is the implication.
She's so young.
I suppose at that age you
have the tendency to get
the wrong idea about
these kinds of things.
[NYGGLATHO] I wouldn't say
it's the "wrong idea," exactly.
You may find this rather
difficult to accept,
but I actually do rate you
quite highly as a man.
[coughing]
[NYGGLATHO] Honestly, I wouldn't
mind being with a man like you.
After all, our races aren't
too terribly different.
And because of that, I might
even be able to provide you
with children of
your own someday.
If I could be a part
of your happiness
in five or ten years' time,
well, there is nothing
I would love more.
[laughs] Now, that being said,
Chtholly's happiness
is a priority for me.
So, don't worry.
I'm not about to go all out
for the kill just yet.
Nevertheless,
she simply can't help
but consider me
a genuine threat.
Oh, I hope that makes sense.
[WILLEM] I'm gonna make a
really despicable request.
What might that be?
Can I pretend that, like,
I didn't hear any of that?
You're right,
that is despicable.
However, it's fine.
I completely understand.
--[PANNIBAL] Hurry!
--[COLLON] Yeah!
Last one there's a loser!
[LAKHESH]
Wait for me!
Hey girls, be careful.
Don't run!
[CHTHOLLY]
Do not run in the halls!
What do you think's
gotten into them, now?
[CHTHOLLY]
Shooting stars.
[GIRLS chattering]
[LAKHESH]
So pretty!
Look over there!
And over there, too!
Oh, yes, spectacular.
Oh, wow. There are
so many tonight.
Did you see that?
Here comes a whole bunch!
[CHTHOLLY, WILLEM laugh]
[gasps]
[TIAT]
Hold it right there!
[BOTH gasp]
But we're gonna miss all
the shooting stars!
Your hair's still wet!
You're supposed to dry it
right after a bath!
Do you wanna catch a cold?
Tiat's got that down.
She's playing "big sis"
to perfection.
It's hard to believe
not too long ago
I was the one running after her.
In fact, she's probably
imitating me.
[WILLEM] Ah, yeah.
I can totally see that.
Thank you.
[WILLEM]
Hm?
For looking out for me.
You know, taking me to
the surface and all that.
[WILLEM] Nah, I'm just doing it
for my own peace of mind.
Don't worry about it.
I don't care.
Thanks, anyway.
--[GIRLS chattering]
--[ALMITA] Look!
[TIAT]
What are you doing, Almita?!
[ALMITA laughs]
[crack]
[TIAT gasps]
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[ALMITA screams]
Almita!
[WILLEM]
Make it!
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[CHTHOLLY grunts]
[crash]
Chtholly!
Chtholly?
Goodness.
Do you realize how
ridiculous you sound?
It's embarrassing.
Some grown-up you are.
You okay, sweetie?
It seems like she's
all right, too.
Chtholly!
[CHTHOLLY]
What are you doing?
Not that I mind.
But let's try this again,
from the top!
[WILLEM] You're not a
leprechaun right now.
[gasps]
You can't generate venenum like
that anymore, don't you get it?
What if things were to go wrong?
What--! What if you...
I thought I was...
I thought I was gonna lose you,
even though I was right here!
[WILLEM cries]
[sighs]
Well, you're one to
talk, aren't you?
I mean, with your
wreck of a body.
I'm perfectly fine.
I am a bit numb perhaps,
but it will go back
to normal in no time.
[WILLEM]
You're not pretending, are you?
No faith in me at all, huh?
You're all banned from the roof!
Get everyone downstairs
immediately!
All right, got it!
[NYGGLATHO] What's going on?
What happened out here?
Nothing too bad.
I'll take her up
to get a bath, now.
Think you can handle
the rest with Nygglatho?
[WILLEM]
Oh, yeah.
[CHTHOLLY]
You ready to go?
[ALMITA]
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
[CHTHOLLY] Tiat is the one
you should apologize to.
If you'd listened to her,
you wouldn't have put
yourself in danger.
[ALMITA]
Right. I know.
I'm sorry.
[CHTHOLLY]
Cover those ears.
Ready to switch?
[ALMITA]
Yep!
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[CHTHOLLY gasping]
[ALMITA]
Chtholly?
What's wrong?
[CHTHOLLY gasping]
[inaudible]
[CHTHOLLY]
Elq.
[CHTHOLLY] Next Episode:
moonlit sorcery.