[NARRATOR]
We swore never to part.
With our vow came euphoria.
[NARRATOR]
My love for him was undeniable.
There was no greater happiness.
[NARRATOR]
Yet, he offered more...
...and I delighted in it.
[NARRATOR] The gifts of love
and bliss he presented to me
were unlike anything
I'd ever known.
My life became his,
and his mine.
He blessed me with his world.
He rewarded me with assurance.
There is no joy ever known
that can compare with my own.
--[bell tolls]
--[CROWD chattering]
[footsteps]
[clanging]
[CROWD gasping]
[BOTH]
Uh?!
Careful! You trying
to hurt someone?
That wasn't me,
so calm yourself!
[CHTHOLLY]
Oh, for crying out loud!
You better stop!
[gasps]
[CHTHOLLY laughs]
I've got you, now!
[CHTHOLLY]
Stop! You're gonna make me fall!
[CROWD gasping]
[CHTHOLLY]
Not enough time for venenum!
[CHTHOLLY screams]
[crash]
[CROWD murmurs]
That hurt.
[gasps] I'm sorry!
Are you, um...
Are your organs intact?
Come back!
[sighs]
[GIRL 1A]
She looks weird, Mommy.
[MOM 1A]
Don't stare, it's rude.
Now, what's this?
Wonder why someone without any
fur would be on this island.
Oh no, I lost my hat!
[PIG MAN 1A]
Get out of here, you freak.
[DEER MAN 1A]
Yeah, get out.
We don't like your kind,
disfeatured.
[CHTHOLLY]
Yes, I'm aware.
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[WILLEM]
Hold on a second.
I'm leaving, okay. Let go.
[WILLEM]
Seriously, hold on.
[WILLEM] I pulled this out
of that little cat's mouth.
Yours, right?
Yes, thanks.
Are you all right?
I'm good. I gather
you must be new here?
[CHTHOLLY]
Yes.
Hope you tolerate
intolerance well.
[gasps]
[CROWD MEMBER 1A]
Is he one, too?
[CROWD MEMBER 1B]
Looks like it.
[CROWD MEMBER 1C]
Seems suspicious to me.
[WILLEM]
Heh. Come on. This way.
[door creaks, bells jingle]
[gasping]
That'll do the trick.
Thank you. So, are you--
This island has no good
food or local specialties.
But you-- [screams]
You may have noticed it's not
very welcoming to those of us
who lack fangs or horns.
Not great for tourism.
Yes, I already know that.
[WILLEM]
Follow me.
I'm sure you've had it
with this place by now.
I'll show you to the port so
you can get off this island.
No, wait!
I appreciate your help.
And I'm...
I'm sorry for all the
trouble I've caused you.
It's just, I--
Well, I realize I have no right
to ask anything of you,
but, um, would you...
[WILLEM] All right,
where do you want to go?
[gasps]
[WILLEM] Is this the view
you were hoping for?
[CHTHOLLY] I've seen
sky islands from higher up
and farther out before,
but gazing down on one
from the heart of the city
like this is brand new.
I've always wanted to do it,
just never really
had the chance.
That so?
But now, I've officially
made my wish a reality,
and I got to make some
great memories, too.
Thank you again for today.
So many wonderful experiences,
and it's all thanks to you.
I think you're giving
me too much credit.
What about them? I'm guessing
they're here for you?
Today's been kinda like a
fairytale, but time's up.
Mind if I make one last request,
fairy godfather?
It's a small one.
I'd appreciate it if you'd
forget you ever met me.
Forget I ever met you...?
[CHTHOLLY laughs]
Farewell!
Curious, but I suppose it's
none of my business anyway.
[WILLEM]
Long time no see, Grick.
How's Anara doing?
[GRICK] He screwed up
big time last month.
Wound up becoming Third food.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
Well, don't be. That's
the life of a salvager.
From the moment we
choose to treasure hunt
on the surface,
we're prepared to die.
That's true.
No need to be sad!
Now, on to happy news.
I think I might be able
to land you work!
Yeah, it's for the military.
Come on, kid!
You could at least pretend
to be excited about this.
They're not lookin' for
special skills or experience.
The only quality they require
is someone who's trustworthy.
[WILLEM]
Hm...
No.
Sorry, but I gotta pass.
You'll have to ask
a different loser.
Look, they're also
insisting on a disfeatured,
with no horns or fur.
You're perfect for this.
In fact, you're the only one
they could hire, and you.
[WILLEM] I said no.
I appreciate how you try
to look out for me,
but I choose to live here
of my own free will.
[GRICK]
I understand.
You wanna keep living
like an outcast.
Dead man walking
and all that, right?
Why try to find something
that makes you happy when
you've already decided
not to be?
I get where you're comin'
from, kid, believe me.
But I can't help it.
I want you to be able to live a
normal life up in these skies.
I want you to accept
what I know.
The dead won't come back.
But you're not dead,
you've still got a life to live!
Look, you can make a ton of
cash on this thing, okay?
Why not at least get all
that debt off your back?
Give yourself a chance
to find the right path.
What's going on with this
coffee, it tastes salty.
[sighs]
Oh, damn it all. Ok, Fine!
So you'll take the job, then?
Yes. You positive
they'll want me?
Did you tell the military
I can't even fight,
let alone kill someone?
Don't worry about that.
You're just gonna be the
caretaker of a warehouse
that holds some
special weaponry.
[WILLEM]
Already sounds like a bad idea.
Wonderful! I'll tell
them you're coming!
Get 'em to fill you
in once you're there.
Ah. Whoa, you're not kidding,
this coffee is salty.
[WILLEM] Would've been nice
to know that the warehouse
was on a different island.
It's Cold.
[wolves howling]
[WILLEM]
Oh, no.
Wolves are the
last thing I need.
It's been a long time since
I felt being a disfeatured
may not be in my best interest.
And now the bridge
is falling apart.
This is great...
Stuck in the middle of nowhere!
[gasps]
[PANNIBAL]
Attack
[PANNIBAL grunting]
Wait!
[PANNIBAL yells]
[PANNIBAL screams]
[splash]
[PANNIBAL grunts]
Pannibal, what do you
think you're doing
running off on your
own like that?
I've taken down a
suspicious individual.
[CHTHOLLY] Right, like there's
even anyone else here.
[gasps]
[WILLEM groaning]
Hey, it's you.
[gasps] I, what, wait,
what are you doing here?
[WILLEM]
Me? Whoa, so many questions.
[sneezes]
First things first. Help me.
[WILLEM]
Something's wrong.
This is nothing like
what Grick said.
[knocking]
Just a minute.
[NYGGLATHO]
Ahh! Ha, ha, ha!
It's been forever, Willem!
Welcome to the secret
weapons warehouse!
Oh, my. Have you
grown a bit taller?
Why are you here
of all places...
...Nygglatho?
Why, you ask.
Why wouldn't I be here, silly?
This is my job, where I work!
[WILLEM]
Damn it. Grick set me up!
[NYGGLATHO] I take it you two
are still good friends?
[WILLEM] Were good friends
is more like it.
[NYGGLATHO] Try to keep it
down while we're inside.
Everyone's in bed
this time of night.
[WILLEM]
"Everyone"?
[NYGGLATHO] Mm-hm! This
warehouse is run jointly by
the Guardian Wings Military and
the Orlandry Merchant Guild.
So, at least on paper,
it requires caretakers
from both parties.
I represent the Orlandry.
You are the military caretaker.
Yes, that much I know.
Oh, you look so yummy
in your uniform!
I feel like I'm choking...
Now, there's really no need
to rain on my parade, is there?
Everyone knows good toppings
only accentuate the
flavor of a dish,
which means to me you're,
at the very least,
twice as appetizing as I
believe I've ever seen you be.
So you're saying my life
is in twice as much danger.
Oh no, oh, ye of little faith.
Have you already forgotten?
While, yes, I may be a
troll and while, yes,
you may be an extremely
rare feast in my eyes,
I have no plan to dig in.
Not yet.
[WILLEM]
Wow. Thanks.
[door slams]
[NYGGLATHO]
Can you imagine the shame?
You're the last of
your kind, after all.
I know better than to waste you
on a passing burst of craving,
no matter how strong.
Of course, if you were to give
me permission to eat you,
I would certainly consider it.
[NYGGLATHO]
Do I have your permission?
Hell, no.
No? Oh, won't you please
consider it some more.
I'd be fine with a
non-dominant arm.
Even a finger would do for now.
Stop it. Can we get down
to business, please?
So, what exactly am
I supposed to do?
Not a damn thing.
Huh?
Wait, you're not planning
to stay on this island,
as well, are you?
Well, obviously. How else will
I do my job as caretaker?
I'm legitimate military, now,
so I'm sticking around.
I only ask because the previous
two caretakers didn't bother
showing up after the first day.
Really?
[NYGGLATHO]
What do you want to do?
You don't have to
stay here, you know.
I can arrange something.
Off-island accommodations,
maybe?
You say that like I won't
get stabbed in the back
the moment I take
my eyes off you.
Wow, so mean!
What kind of monster
do you take me for?
[WILLEM]
The kind that eats people.
Anyway, I'm just not
one of those guys
who quits a job
they've committed to.
I fully intend to
stay right here.
Uh! Oh, I had a feeling
I could count on you!
It'll be fun after so long to
get to take care of you again.
That makes me kinda happy.
[WILLEM] Don't get
the wrong idea, Willem.
This isn't about a man and a
woman spending time together.
It's about a troll trying to
fatten a tasty-looking lamb
before she devours it.
Care to share what
that scary look is for?
Just to confirm.
You're not planning
to eat me, correct?
No, I'm not.
Genuinely, my only desire
is to take care of you.
Don't you know that trolls are
bound by their natural instinct
to serve every guest
with dedication?
Trust me. I swear I won't
try to eat you, yet.
So, in return...
Let me use my other instinct!
Can we get back to the topic?
This building is the
weapon warehouse
I'm supposed look after,
is that right?
[NYGGLATHO]
You're so mean to me.
And yes, this is the building.
But it looks nothing
like a warehouse.
Where do they store all the guns
and artillery in here?
Let's continue the
discussion tomorrow.
It has gotten rather late.
Plus, the naughty
walls have ears.
--[LAKHESH] I'm sorry!
--[TIAT] Hey! Stop shoving me!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Oh, hi, Nygglatho.
Thanks for having us!
Yes! Please, have us!
Get back to your rooms, ladies.
'Kay, but before we do,
we think it'd be nice
to properly greet
the new caretaker.
Go now, or I'll eat you.
[ALL whimpering]
[ALL]
Goodnight, Miss Nygglatho.
[NYGGLATHO]
Goodnight, girls!
Well, how about I show
you to your room, then?
It kinda seems like I'm not
the only one allergic to you.
[gasps] Oh, you big meanie.
[sighs] All, right.
If anything, this
place is unexpected.
[ALMARIA] Poppa!
Hey, Pops?
Sheesh, Poppa, how long are you
planning to stay asleep for?
[crash]
[TIAT]
You think he's asleep?
[LAKHESH] Don't ask me.
I've never seen a man before.
[PANNIBAL] We should probably
keep it down, guys.
[GIRLS yelp]
[TIAT] Why do you always have to
shove me around like that, gah!
[PANNIBAL] Hey, caretaker.
Beautiful night, isn't it?
We're here!
[WILLEM]
Shh! Nygglatho will hear you.
[GIRLS]
Shh!
So, who might you girls be?
--My name's Collon!
--I'm Pannibal.
[gasps] If you talk at the
same time, he can't hear you!
Sorry, I'm Lakhesh.
[WILLEM] Collon, Pannibal,
Tiat, and Lakhesh.
Okay, I think I've got
your names down.
[GIRLS gasping]
Where'd you come from, mister?
What's your name?
[GIRLS chattering]
And out of all these questions
you've been asked,
which one will you choose
to answer first?
I guess I might as well
go with your question
to start this thing off.
Spicy meat dishes are
usually my favorite,
and I can't stand
reptrace cuisine.
Nygglatho and I are basically
a farmer and her lost lamb.
And I lived on Island
Twenty-Eight until this morning.
[GIRLS gasping]
[WILLEM]
My name's Willem Kmetsch.
You can call me Willem.
I hope you girls like me.
I'll be living here.
Wait, you mean you're
gonna stay?
[WILLEM]
Probably.
[GIRLS]
Ohh!
[WILLEM]
It's not that big of a deal.
Oh, but it is.
You have to understand, none of
the caretakers with the military
have ever lived here before.
Yeah, Nygglatho did
mention that.
[CHTHOLLY]
Oh, good grief.
How could you possibly think
this was a good idea?
You were clearly told to
give him space, weren't you?
[TIAT]
Um, we sort of, uh...
[COLLON]
Curiosity got the best of us!
You should have known better.
We don't have the kind of
power to resist Curiosity!
Should I let Nygglatho know?
[GIRLS whimpering]
--[TIAT] Have a good night!
--[PANNIBAL] Goodnight!
[COLLON]
Nice to meet you, Willem.
See you tomorrow!
I swear, those girls.
Sorry about that.
The little ones tend to get
pretty worked up.
I don't mind at all.
I'm actually used to
dealing with children.
But, what are they doing here?
Well, whatever you do, try not
to spoil them too much, okay?
We don't want it going right to
their heads, and it will, so...
[WILLEM chuckles]
I'll try.
[WILLEM]
Huh?
Oh, um. So, about Pannibal.
Sorry she attacked you.
She didn't mean anything by it.
For what it's worth,
I'm not mad.
You provided hot water
immediately,
so I even avoided
getting a cold.
Good. Good.
One more thing.
Um...
Chtholly.
That's my name. It's Chtholly.
[WILLEM]
Mm?
It's really belated.
You know, because the time
we've spent in the town
with the fairy tale thing and
the cat, and never mind...
Oh, right. Gotcha.
It's a pleasure. I'm Willem.
Oh, yep.
I know.
I was told that.
[CHTHOLLY]
Anyway. Sorry to disturb you.
Good night.
Wait, just for a minute.
There's something I'm
kind of confused about.
Real quick.
My understanding is
I'm a caretaker
for special military weapons.
[CHTHOLLY]
Correct.
And we're in a warehouse,
a warehouse that's used
to store those weapons?
[CHTHOLLY]
That's right.
[WILLEM] Then why does this
look absolutely nothing
like a warehouse? Why don't I
see a single weapon anywhere?
And, for the love of
all things confusing,
please at least answer this...
Who are you girls?
And why are you living
in a military facility.
[gasps] Did you take this job
without knowing we were here?
Yeah.
And you spent time
with the little ones
without knowing anything?
Yeah.
Let me, take a wild guess.
You're one of those people
who just goes with
the flow, aren't you?
[WILLEM grunting]
[CHTHOLLY sighs]
Oh, very well.
I can clear this up. The answer
to the first set of questions
lies in the second set, and the
answer to the second set,
well...
It lies in the first set!
Yeah, real clear.
[CHTHOLLY]
Try not to over think it.
The truth is, it's us.
We are the special weapons you
were sent here to care for.
[WILLEM]
What...?
Make sense?
We're all so glad you've come.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll be our new caretaker!
[ALMARIA]
Here you go.
Thank you, looks good!
I'm so hungry!
Should be as good as it looks.
Come on! It's the night before
the final battle, Pops!
Nothing interesting to say?
Huh, like what?
"Once this war ends, I'll get
married and have kids,"
y'know, somethin' like that?
Yeah, I dunno.
Seems like asking for bad luck.
Why, because it's the kind
of thing characters always
like to say right before
they're killed?
When they get taken out in the
beginning it's supposed to be
more dramatic. I understand
that reasoning. I really do,
but I think it's sadder
when characters you're
attached to die.
[ALMARIA]
Either way, though.
Must be awful to get killed
off because the creator's
just an idiot. No matter
their absurd reasoning.
Well, yeah.
Now, Pops, you're heading
into the final battle,
which means we need
to find you inspiration.
Something concrete you can
hold on to in order to survive!
You know, like a reason
to come back here.
Anything'll do.
[ALMARIA]
You've gotta find one.
You've got to.
Because if you don't,
I'm afraid I won't be able to
send you off with a smile.
[WILLEM]
Butter cake.
Do what?
Yeah, your butter cakes
are pretty incredible.
You should bake an extra-large
one for my next birthday.
For real?
You'll fight to return alive
just to eat some cake?
Why, you got a
problem with that?
No, I don't. I just
thought that maybe...
[ALMARIA]
Fine, whatever.
I'll settle for butter cake.
In return, since you
suggested it,
I'll feed you so much
of that cake
you're bound to get heartburn.
[NARRATOR 1A]
Unfortunately, the young fighter
would never return home.
Less than a year later
his world would be gone,
and humanity would be decimated.
[WILLEM] Next Episode:
late autumn night's dream.