Just try not to over
think it, okay?
The truth of the matter is, it's
us.
We're the special weapons.
You get to care for us.
[WILLEM gasping]
[GIRLS chattering]
So, what's after breakfast?
Play?
[CHTHOLLY]
We're the special weapons.
--Stop it that's mine!
--No, it's not it's mine!
Go find somewhere
to sit so you can eat.
Hey! No running!
[GIRLS laughing]
[NYGGLATHO]
Good morning, ladies.
Your attention, please.
[GIRLS gasp]
These girls, they're
the special weapons.
Allow me to introduce you.
This gentleman is Second-Grade
Technical Officer Willem,
and he will be living
with us from now on.
I'm very pleased
to meet you all.
[GIRLS whimper]
Uh.
[bell tolls]
[WILLEM yawns]
You three are awake early!
[GIRLS gasping]
You up for a duel?
No, thanks.
[LAKHESH grunting]
Should be easier, now.
[GIRL 2C]
Lakhesh's gonna get eaten!
Or kidnapped for ransom!
I'm not gonna get kidnapped.
I'm not, right?
Please put me down.
[GIRL 2F laughing]
This way!
Hi.
[GIRLS gasp, scream]
[WILLEM]
Uh.
Don't take it personally.
The children here aren't used
to having adult men around,
so they don't know how
to interact with one.
Yes, I understand that.
I just wish I knew a way to
keep from terrifying them.
Honestly, it's depressing.
[ITHEA]
Well, of course it would be!
So, Officer Willem, you like
little girls, do ya?
I like kids, yes.
[ITHEA]
Wow. Then, you admit it.
Now, I'm dying to know
which one is your type!
There's me, the lovably
boisterous Ithea.
Capricious lil' Nephren here.
Although, if I were to
make a recommendation,
I'd say go with
fresh-faced and moody.
[WILLEM]
Chtholly. We've met.
Hold on, when did that happen?
Moving a bit fast, aren't ya?
You gotta tell me everything!
[CHTHOLLY]
Cut it out, Ithea!
Okay, it's been cut.
I find you three and all
the little ones very cute.
[CHTHOLLY] What? You're
lumping me in with children?
You're not much older than them.
That's not true!
I'll have you know
I'm 15 years old!
And now I wanna know
if that falls within
the officer's range.
[CHTHOLLY]
Ithea, shut up!
Back to the point, I wish I
could think of a good way
to get the little ones
to open up to me.
[WILLEM yelps]
Even when you're
agonizing like that,
you... look... delicious.
Nygglatho! What's that?
You're supposed to be the adult.
You can't just go around
licking people!
Great plan! I bet
something tasty
will win 'em over real fast!
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
Is that what she meant?!
[gasping]
[WILLEM]
Of course!
[ITHEA, NEPHREN]
Uh?
That's perfect!
So you can cook, huh?
I guess just a bit.
[ITHEA] A man who can
help around the house
is definitely a keeper!
[NEPHREN]
Valid.
Where'd you pick up that
so-called wisdom?
Looks good.
Here, tell me what you think.
I'll pass, thanks, though.
[WILLEM]
Really?
All right.
It's yummy.
[GIRLS cheering]
What do you think?
Ready to dig in, girls?
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
[GIRL]
This is the bestest, ever!
You've certainly
changed, haven't you?
Not that I didn't love it,
but before, you were always
what I considered one of those
"aloof degenerate" types.
--Is something wrong?
--Yeah.
I forgot who I was for
just a moment there.
Won't happen again.
It won't?
Oh my.
[GIRLS]
Seconds, please!
--Whoa!
--[GIRLS chattering, laughing]
[GIRLS chattering]
What was that about
forgetting who you were?
[CHTHOLLY]
I think it's safe to say
you got them to open up to you.
I did. Kids are funny.
They're just great.
Hearts on their sleeves.
Very true.
Oh, by the way.
You didn't have to help me
clean up, but thank you.
You're welcome.
It's a good distraction.
Uh. What do you mean?
Do you need a distraction?
No, not really.
I think we're finally done!
Yay! Cleanup complete!
Goodnight, then.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[CHTHOLLY]
Okay. Goodnight.
[COLLON]
Here we go!
[GIRLS chattering]
[GIRL 2F]
All right, it's my turn, now!
[GIRL 2C]
No, I'm throwing it!
Girls, that's enough,
stop fighting.
Calm down. Don't be weird.
[ITHEA]
Can't stop thinking about him?
[CHTHOLLY yelps]
Wow, interesting reaction.
Why are you acting like that?!
[laughs] Acting like what?
I just think it's funny
how everyone's taken
to Willem so fast.
I mean, it's practically like
he's already been here
for years, ya know?
Yes, I do.
[NEPHREN]
I like your new hat.
It must mean a lot considering
you keep it safely
hidden in your closet.
[ITHEA] Oh. Yeah,
she's obsessed with it.
Uh! No, it doesn't mean
anything to me.
I just prefer to keep
it out of the way
because you don't need a
hat like that very often.
Yeah, right.
[CHTHOLLY]
What do you mean by that?
[ITHEA]
What do you mean what do I mean?
Hey, Ren, you interested
in him, too?
[NEPHREN]
Not really.
Though I do find him...
curious, I suppose.
[ITHEA] Meaning, you're
interested in him.
[ITHEA] Chtholly.
How many days are
left as of now?
Around ten.
I don't know if that's enough
time for a romance, but,
you might as well give
it a shot, you know?
Will you please leave it alone?
[ITHEA]
Don't be so timid.
In this day and age,
lots of fairies never
even hit adolescence.
You did that and fell in love,
which basically means
you won life.
[CHTHOLLY]
It isn't like that.
[NEPHREN]
I see. I'll search the study
for any books that might
help in this endeavor.
[CHTHOLLY]
Oh, not you, too.
Ugh! Don't bother!
[CHTHOLLY] Can we focus
and get dressed already?
[ITHEA]
Is that not what we're doing?
Never saw it comin'. Hi-yah!
[TIAT yelps]
[LAKHESH]
Collon, what are you thinking?
Tiat's on your team!
[GIRL 2G giggles]
Whatever works.
I got it!
[ALMITA laughs]
Stop rolling, ball!
[gasps]
[WILLEM]
Almita!
Hey!
Almita! Are you all right?
[ALMITA]
Yeah. I think so.
Ouchie.
[gasps]
I fell down hard!
[laughs]
Stay still. You're bleeding.
[ALMITA]
I'm fine, don't worry.
[COLLON]
Almita! Get the dumb ball!
It's right over there!
[gasps]
[COLLON laughs]
Hurry up!
You girls are...
You appear to have something
you'd like to share with me.
I didn't realize it
until earlier today.
These children.
They're not at all concerned
about their lives.
[NYGGLATHO]
They're not.
I know it can be unnerving
how indifferent they are.
[WILLEM]
It's not normal.
Who and what are these girls?
I get why you ask, but, to be
honest, I'd rather not answer.
Are you sure you wanna
know the truth?
Once you know, your attitude
towards them will change,
and you won't be able
to help yourself.
I just...
I don't want that change in you
to hurt their feelings.
The past few days, you've acted
like a very nice young man.
While, at first, I found that
side of you a little creepy,
now, I'm thankful for how kind
and generous you've been.
If it's at all possible,
I'd like things to stay this
way for a while longer.
[sighs]
I want to know.
[NYGGLATHO] I assume you're
already aware of the 17 beasts?
[WILLEM] Yes, they were created
500 years ago by foolish humans.
I mean, emnetwihts.
Awfully self-deprecating,
aren't we?
Of course, not long
after their creation,
the beasts wiped out all
life on the surface,
including the emnetwihts.
That wasn't enough
for the beasts, though.
Our skies are in constant
jeopardy of their next attack.
Which begs the question,
how do we defend
ourselves against them?
The answer lies
beyond this door.
[door creaks]
[gasps] Are those... carillons?
[NYGGLATHO] We call them
"dug weapons" now.
These instruments are our only
means of fighting the 17 beasts.
[WILLEM]
Insania.
Ignareo.
Percival.
[WILLEM]
As I recall,
Carillons were special.
So special, in fact,
that only chosen emnetwiht
braves could wield them.
[NYGGLATHO]
Correct.
[WILLEM] So, with the
emnetwihts gone now,
how are they still working?
Who's using them to fight?
Well, surely, you already know.
[WILLEM]
But how...?
[NYGGLATHO]
The girls are leprechauns.
Fairies who have imitated
emnetwihts since ancient times.
That means they have the ability
to use emnetwiht weapons.
The difference?
Their bodies were created
to be expended in battle.
ecause of that, they have
no fear of death.
You wanted to know
what they were.
You have your answer.
I hope you can handle it.
I'll be fine.
So those girls are your
partners, now?
Huh.
[bell tolls]
Pannibal, you're going too fast!
[GIRLS chattering]
[GIRL 2I]
Wait!
[GIRLS laughing]
Hello, Nephren. All alone?
Where are Chtholly and Ithea?
They both went out.
[gasps]
[WILLEM]
They both went out,
and did not return
until several days later.
[WILLEM] Venenum output
is inversely proportional
to a spell caster's life force.
The more they want to live,
the lower the output.
For those who care
nothing about their lives,
the output rises drastically.
[WILLEM]
Such power cannot be contained
and quickly grows out of control
causing a massive explosion.
Both spell caster and
enemy will be obliterated,
leaving the dug weapon as
the lone survivor of the blast.
[WILLEM]
Yes.
I'm sure those girls
make excellent weapons.
If it isn't Officer Willem.
Long time no see!
Hey, are you two all right?
What?! Yeah, sure, I'm fine!
And she's...
Well, she's napping
'cause she's worn out.
That's a relief.
[ITHEA] Fancy running
into you here, though.
Out on a walk?
[WILLEM]
Nygglatho told me you were back,
so I'm here to pick you up.
[ITHEA] Wait, does that
mean that you, um...
Knew that you were
away fighting?
Seventeen beasts and all that.
[ITHEA laughs]
I can't believe it!
Talk about embarrassing.
[LIMESKIN]
You must be who I'm looking for.
Technical Officer Willem,
that correct?
Yes.
And who exactly are you?
[LIMESKIN] I'm here to
give you their weapons.
Return them to
the vault immediately.
[WILLEM] These are Seniorious
and Valgulious, right?
[ITHEA] Wow! You're
good at knowing stuff.
Seniorious is the one
Chtholly's compatible with.
And I've got Valgulious.
Seriously, you're
extremely well informed.
I bet you checked our equipment
list or something like that.
Actually, no.
They just happen to be swords
I'm familiar with, that's all.
That's all, huh?
Very interesting.
Fess up. How much
do you really know?
[WILLEM]
Not much.
I know that you're fairies.
And you fight with dug weapons
to protect the world.
I suppose that's about it.
[ITHEA] Did the idea of
weapons that look like us
bother you at all?
I mean, we're basically
disposable lives.
Not to mention, we use relics of
those awful emnetwihts.
[ITHEA]
What's up?
[WILLEM]
A long time ago,
I knew someone in a
similar situation.
And I owe that someone a
great deal for many things.
So after hearing your story,
I couldn't just walk away.
Now, you know.
Oh, boy!
A sudden mention of your past!
Two people having a
heart-to-heart all alone!
Wait, are you hitting on
and or flirting with me?
All alone?
Are you forgetting about
the girl on my back?
[ITHEA] Course not!
Because this is the start
of a love triangle filled with
passion, hate, and jealousy.
[WILLEM] Keep it down.
You're gonna wake her up.
[ITHEA]
Wow, what a tease.
[gasps]
Willem!
What do you think
you're doing in here?
I think I'm taking
care of a patient.
Well, who's your patient?
[gasping]
Try not to push yourself.
You do still have a fever.
I'm your caretaker, remember.
So, let me take care.
I don't need you,
a caretaker or not.
Besides, what you do for me
doesn't really matter anyway.
I appreciate it, but I
don't have much time left.
"Time left"?
What does that mean?
[CHTHOLLY]
Hey...
What is it?
Just um, let's say...
...if I were gonna die in five
days, like hypothetically,
do you think you'd be
a little nicer to me?
What are you talking about?
[CHTHOLLY]
In five days, Island Fifteen
will come under a powerful
timere attack.
[WILLEM]
One of the 17 beasts?
[CHTHOLLY]
None of the beasts can fly.
But a timere can release parts
of its body into the air,
allowing those parts to
travel all the way up
to the sky islands.
How do you know for
sure it will be five days?
We can predict
their attacks, now.
We've fought for centuries.
I guess we're bound to evolve.
But it certainly
took us long enough!
Apparently, the incoming
timere can't be fought
using usual military methods.
However, a fairy wielding
a dug weapon...
...can take it out
single-handedly.
The only cost would
be your life.
[CHTHOLLY]
That's pretty much it.
If I use my power and
Seniorious to blow myself up,
I'll just barely be able
to destroy the thing.
How lucky is that, right?
Nobody else will have to die.
Okay, so it's not hypothetical.
Does that maybe make you feel
like granting me a final wish?
[WILLEM]
Depends on what it is.
Well, I uh...
Um.
Like for example.
What if I...
[gasps]
A kiss?
What if I asked to kiss you?
Just once.
[WILLEM exhales]
[footsteps]
After all that talk about
only having five days left,
that's the kind of
crap you ask me for?
[gasps] So what!
Ah!
Ow.
You're a kid.
Why are you trying to be
something you're not?
Excuse me?!
What's wrong with wanting to
have sweet memories before I go?
I'm about to die here!
But first, I wanna matter!
I wanna be kept alive
in someone else's heart!
Just to be connected.
Tell me! What's wrong with that?
Am I not allowed anything?
I don't want you to sell
yourself short, that's all.
You don't have to settle for
who's standing in front of you.
You should buy me while
I'm selling myself short.
Seriously, it's a basic
rule for shopping smart.
Just go!
If you won't kiss me,
don't try to help!
I'm not even crying!
Well, you sound like
you're crying.
[CHTHOLLY]
You're crying!
Good grief.
Look, I want you to turn
on your belly for a sec.
[CHTHOLLY]
I can't hear you.
[WILLEM] Will you please
stop being difficult?
[CHTHOLLY]
I said I can't hear you!
Oh, come on.
Could you be any more stubborn?
[gasps]
[CHTHOLLY]
What... What was that?
Um, I didn't um...
I really didn't feel that one.
[gasping]
[whimpers]
[WILLEM]
I knew it.
You're showing typical symptoms
of venenum poisoning.
You generated too
much which then
gave you a real nasty
case of muscular fever.
This isn't pleasant,
but it helps.
[CHTHOLLY]
Ow! By not pleasant,
you mean it feels like fire?!
It'll be better in a little bit.
[groans] A little bit?
I'm gonna feel like this
forever, aren't I?
[CHTHOLLY groaning]
[CHTHOLLY gasps]
[CHTHOLLY screams]
Not to worry. You just
let me take care of this.
[LILA] The mightiest brave is
here with the mightiest sword.
There's nothing
else for you to do.
[WILLEM]
No.
I can't just walk away.
[WILLEM] Next Episode:
starry road to tomorrow.