[GIRLS chattering]
[COLLON]
H'yah!
[GIRL 2F grunting]
[CHTHOLLY shivers]
[CHTHOLLY]
It's so cold.
Where'd this come from?
[NYGGLATHO]
Chtholly? Are you up yet?
[NOPHT] Ugh, I'm bored.
I'm bored. I'm bored.
I'm so bored, bored,
bored, bored, bored!
Nopht, stop. Please be quiet.
Come on, I know you've
gotta be bored, too, Rhan.
What is that? Ancient book?
Yes, one of yesterday's finds.
Are you telling me you can
read emnetwiht writing?
I can connect the dots
between the words.
After that, it's just
an educated guess.
Ah. Well?
What are the emnetwihts saying?
[RHANTOLK]
The human race...
should have...
never come into being.
The visitors were who created
them, and the cost was great.
The gods failed. Blame the gods.
They failed us.
It was their biggest mistake.
That's crazy.
Remember, this isn't 100%.
It's a best guess.
[RHANTOLK]
Beasts by humans.
Truth unleash.
Oh, this might be
the other way around.
Humans unleash the beasts,
and fill the world with,
with the ashen truth.
Oh wow!
Yes, I know. Now, get off me.
Sounds to me like your
book is talking about
the beasts destroying
the surface.
Like a prophecy.
Something wild like that.
It's not.
This seems to be a fairy tale
or a textbook of sorts.
I think it's more likely
humans created the beasts
in accordance with this idea.
At least, that would be
the natural assumption.
Yeah, it makes sense.
[NOPHT]
Uh?
However, it almost seems like...
[NOPHT groans]
[knocking]
Who's there?
[GRICK] Hey, I'm looking
for the waiting room
for the fleet escort.
Is this it?
I'm a salvager with
your fellow passengers,
the Orlandry Merchant Guild.
Everybody calls me Grick,
'cause it's my name.
[TIAT]
Chtholly!
I'm so happy you're not a ghost!
Oh, Tiat...
Sorry, she hasn't fully
recovered from everything yet.
Poor thing was out of sorts
the entire time you were broken.
So, please be patient
with her outburst.
[TIAT]
I was.
I don't know why.
For some reason,
I just felt so down.
I see. I also see that
you've grown taller.
[door opens]
[GIRLS chattering]
[gasps]
Hello, Chtholly!
You're all better now, right?
Well, good morning.
You feelin' okay?
Uh. Uh-huh.
Good morning.
[LAKHESH]
Are you going on a trip?
Is that why you're
wearing your hat?
Oh, no.
My hair refused to cooperate
today, so I'm trying to hide it.
Anyway, tell me how
practice was this morning!
Piece of cake!
[stomach growls]
Oh, I made me hungry.
[GIRLS chattering]
[NYGGLATHO]
That's enough, girls.
Breakfast will be ready
when you're ready.
Meaning after you've
all washed up.
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
All right, let's make
our escape now.
Not eating breakfast with us?
Just in case,
I want her to get checked out
as soon as possible.
Of course.
Um, bye.
[RHANTOLK] So you're the survey
unit's adviser, then?
That's me.
I figured I should at
least come greet those
who hold my life in their hands!
Can't hurt to be
nice to the ones
in charge of protecting my crew!
[NOPHT]
That's a weird thing to say.
We look like we're
beast fighters?
You can't honestly believe
the two of us can protect you.
Frankly, no, not at all.
It's still hard
for me to accept.
Really, it seems as if it's
some kind of stupid joke.
But the thing is,
you're here and you've
got dug weapons with you.
Matches everything I've heard
about your kind too perfectly.
Whadda they call you again?
Leprechauns?
That's right.
You sure do know a whole lot.
I have a couple of friends who
keep me pretty well informed.
Now. Here, I brought you
a token of friendship!
You haven't been home
in more than a month.
I bet you miss good food.
Picked these up on Island
Thirty-One on my way here.
Hope you like meat pies!
[gasping]
You can't possibly be serious!
I'll have you know our favor
is not so easily bought.
We'll gladly take them.
Rhan, how can you say that?
As it turns out, at the moment
we have nothing in
particular to do.
We could talk to him for a bit.
I think there's no harm in that.
Whatever.
It's fine with me if
it's fine with you!
[RHANTOLK]
Now, then.
"Grick," was it?
That's right.
[RHANTOLK] Have you been
a salvager very long?
Yeah, I suppose you
could say that.
Really?
Have you ever run into a beast?
[gasps]
Huh? Why would you ask that
question, you actually think
you can learn something about
those things from me?
[RHANTOLK]
Yes.
I want to know more.
To start with, what are they?
Where and how were
the beasts even born?
Why did they wipe out the
emnetwihts on the surface?
You seem to care an
awful lot about them.
Yes, while the beasts may
threaten your very existence,
they are the reason for ours.
Isn't it natural to be curious
about one's origin?
[NYGGLATHO]
I would learn a lot more
if I could just bite off a
little piece of your flesh.
[CHTHOLLY]
Please don't.
Nygglatho.
Is there anything wrong?
Like with my body, I mean.
[NYGGLATHO]
Hm. Is there something wrong?
Don't worry, I wouldn't
call it "wrong."
Thanks for shopping with me.
It was nice.
I appreciate you carrying
the stuff back, too.
I also had an errand to run,
so don't even mention it.
From what I understand,
you've been working at that
bakery for quite a while.
How did that happen?
[LAKHESH] The military brass
did not like the idea at all,
but Nygglatho helped convince
them to let me do it.
And what do you think,
Officer Willem?
How do you feel about us
weapons working for money?
Is there something wrong
with wanting to be like
everyone else?
I feel like grown-ups are
supposed to ensure that kids
can do whatever they
want within reason.
As long as it's not dangerous or
plain wrong, it's okay with me.
[gasps] Thank you!
Oh, I love you so much,
Officer Willem!
I've never had a father before,
but you seem like what
a father should be.
That's sweet to say.
I actually already consider
you girls to be my kids,
more or less.
You really do?
Hold on, if you're our father,
then what person would
that make our mother?
Maybe Nygglatho?
Doesn't seem fair to Chtholly.
All right, time to get going.
I have to start
the cooking, now.
[door closes]
[NYGGLATHO]
I gave you the silver test,
and it came up negative.
It did? Wow, okay.
What does that mean?
Silver powder has a natural
reaction to irregular death.
To put it simply,
it's a drug we use
to detect the
presence of spirits.
And since leprechauns
are a type of spirit,
I was expecting your blood
to turn black immediately
after I mixed it together with
the silver testing agent.
But there was no
reaction at all.
I don't know the reason,
but right now,
your body is not scientifically
a leprechaun's.
Wait! What are you
talking about?
Then, what's happened
to my body?!
I have no idea.
It's just the only conclusion
that I can make, well,
based on the findings.
Is that... Is that why
my hair is changing?
[NYGGLATHO]
There's the possibility
it could be a side
effect of your coma.
Nygglatho, what's going
to happen to me?
[NYGGLATHO]
You honestly don't feel anything
wrong with your body?
No, I don't.
I feel perfectly normal.
Well, then. I guess try not
to worry about it for now.
Give me time to do
a little more research.
I'll figure it out.
And don't get any ideas
about dyeing your hair.
I doubt that it's gonna
bother Willem.
[gasps] Why would you say that?!
--[ding]
--Uh?
[NYGGLATHO] Until we get
all of this cleared up,
I want you to be sure and stay
away from your dug weapon.
There's just no telling
what might happen.
All right. I can do that.
Although, what am I gonna do
if I can't wield a sword?
[NYGGLATHO]
I dunno.
Maybe you can work on
getting married instead?
[gasps]
I'm being serious here.
Surely, you realize Willem's
contract will eventually expire.
Of course,
we both know how he is.
I'm certain he would stay
if we all asked him.
Then, can't we just do that?
Of course not!
Asking is way too easy.
Instead, we'll
aggressively remind him
that this is his home.
Then, no one will have
to ask him at all!
And obviously, the best way
to make him feel like
this is his home is for him
to have a wife and family.
What? Is that how
this stuff really works?
That is how this stuff works.
Honestly, I was considering
volunteering myself for the job
in question, but I thought--
[CHTHOLLY]
Please don't!
If you did, then...
then I wouldn't stand a chance.
I suppose it's time for you
to start fishing.
You better work some magic
and hook that man fast.
Don't procrastinate, either.
Otherwise, me or some other girl
will get him before you do.
[GIRLS chattering]
[GIRLS]
Time to dig in!
Whoa! It's heaven.
[ITHEA] You're a little
too good at this stuff, T.O.
What does that mean?
You knew she wouldn't eat it if
you only baked some for her,
so you found a way to make sure
she had her cake and ate it.
I gotta say, I'm impressed you
baked enough for all of us!
Pretty good,
if I do say so myself.
Hey, Ren. Where is she?
Um, probably her room.
Why, did something happen?
[NEPHREN] No, she just
prefers not to eat sweets
in front of anyone else.
[ITHEA] Mm-hm. She likes
to think she's fancy.
But, it's not as if it
bothers her that much.
You should totally take some
to her room yourself
and spend some sugary-sweet
"quality" time together.
Heh.
Don't make it sound
inappropriate.
[CHTHOLLY]
It's just, I dunno.
The other girls look up to me,
so I don't want to look
childish in front of them.
And um, from what
I've been told,
when I eat stuff like that...
...let's just say that I
could ruin my own reputation.
With sweets, I kinda go crazy.
What is that look for?
You're making a really big deal
out of something
that's ridiculous,
which sorta proves that
you're still a kid.
[CHTHOLLY]
Excuse me?!
Shall I also get you some tea?
Well, my lady?
[laughs]
[WILLEM]
Heh.
[CHTHOLLY inhales]
[sighs]
It smells so delicious.
It is.
Looks delicious.
Yes, that's because it is.
You sure?
Like, it's okay for me to eat
this in front of you?
Do you even need to ask?
Who do you think I
baked it for, silly?
I kept my promise. [cries]
I did it.
[CHTHOLLY sobs]
[WILLEM]
Must've been rough.
[CHTHOLLY]
Yes.
Yes!
It was, it was so hard.
[WILLEM]
I know I said this yesterday,
but welcome home, Chtholly.
[CHTHOLLY cries]
I'm home.
I made it back. [sobs]
I finally got to say it.
[WILLEM]
And I finally got to hear it.
[CHTHOLLY cries]
[CHTHOLLY]
Does it look weird?
The red hair?
[WILLEM laughs]
It's a very pretty color,
and it looks great.
Oh, good. Thank you.
[CHTHOLLY]
All right. I'm fine now.
You sure about that?
You're not feeling
sick or anything?
I'll be mad at you
if you push yourself.
[CHTHOLLY]
I'm fine!
And I have cooking, laundry,
and lots of other
responsibilities to focus on.
[WILLEM]
There's no reason to get upset.
[CHTHOLLY]
I know.
Just wait. I hope
that you're ready!
[GIRL 2I]
That's what I said!
Ladies! Did you
forget something?
Like wiping your shoes off
before coming inside?!
[GIRLS]
Huh? Sorry, Chtholly.
[CHTHOLLY] If I'm really freed
from being a fairy soldier...
If I'm really allowed
to pursue my dreams,
the same dreams as most
normal people, then...
I want to live, standing
side by side with him.
I want to see the same things,
walk down the same path,
eat the same food, and go to
the same places he goes.
I want to spend my whole life
that way, with him.
Getting better at homey
stuff is all well and good,
but I mean like...?
It's only for Willem?
[sneezes]
Look at who's making
another spicy meat dish!
[ITHEA]
And seems to me this one's
tailored to a certain
someone's taste buds, too.
Oh, shut up and get
out of here!
Only the person cooking is
allowed in the kitchen anyway!
It's a very pretty color,
and it looks great.
Ooh-hoo.
What? You were eavesdropping!
Ha, ha! Amazing how girls in
love are so full of life!
What?!
Although, I don't know about
hogging the whole kitchen.
I mean, that sure
is a lot of work
just to get to one
guy's stomach.
[LIMESKIN]
How is said fairy soldier?
[NYGGLATHO] It's been around
five days since she woke up,
and so far, she seems fine.
[LIMESKIN]
Does she?
Good, that's wonderful to hear.
Uh, so...
What's with the getup?
[LIMESKIN]
They're civilian clothes.
I happen to be under suspension
for leading a losing battle.
I can't wear a
uniform right now.
Hopefully, this is
only temporary.
Uh-huh. So uh,
why are we making off-duty
lizards come all this way?
What's this conversation about?
To discuss Chtholly's
immediate future, right?
Did I not mention
that to you earlier?
I thought we three
needed to talk about it.
[LIMESKIN]
Hm?
Those girls are
technically weapons.
It's not like they can retire.
And, although Chtholly is not
a leprechaun at the moment,
she's still considered
a fairy soldier on paper.
Which means she can't turn down
an order to sortie, huh.
So then what about on your end?
You're first officer, could you
adjust the sortie lineup?
I could if I was in charge,
but there's a chance the order
might come from higher up
in the command.
Hold on.
You know the Great Sage?
Doesn't he have
military influence?
--[NYGGLATHO] Huh?
--[LIMESKIN] What?
Yes, I know him.
He's the military's top advisor,
everyone knows the Great Sage.
[WILLEM]
Then make sure he receives
a report that goes like this:
"In order to research
leprechaun physiology,
Technical Officer Kmetsch
has chosen soldier
Chtholly Nota Seniorious
to be a test subject."
[NYGGLATHO]
What is that about?
Just call it a hunch.
If I ask to be given
responsibility for her,
I bet he'll agree to it.
Mostly because he'll assume
that'll make me owe him one.
So what kind of relationship
do you imagine you have
with the Great Sage?
Don't worry about that,
worry about how we're
going to replace Chtholly.
Ithea and Ren can't handle it,
not if they're by themselves.
Oh.
Right, well, about that.
There's, uh...
[BOTH]
Hm?
[NYGGLATHO]
I heard from the guild
that beasts attacked
the surface survey team.
Apparently,
the Saxifraga was sunk.
Saxi...
It sunk? What of the warriors
that were aboard?
Both were a bit worn out,
however, apparently unhurt.
[WILLEM]
Hang on a second, you guys.
"Survey team"? "Both"?
Oh, yeah.
I keep forgetting that you only
arrived here like a month ago.
Do you actually know how
many battle-ready fairies
we currently have?
Aside from Chtholly, three.
That's with Tiat, who hasn't
been paired with a sword.
No, we have five girls ready.
There's Ithea, and
Nephren, Tiat, I guess.
We also have Nopht and Rhantolk.
Well, where are those
girls right now?
You could try putting
two and two together?
No way...
Yes way.
I think that's correct, but
how can we really know...
[RABBIT SOLDIER 7A]
What is that?
It's a Beast!
[PIG SOLDIER 7A
whimpers, groans]
[DOG SOLDIER 7A whimpers]
[GRICK grunts]
You idiot!
That thing reacts
to sound and motion.
Just be still and keep quiet.
Come on. What the hell
is goin' on over there?
Huh? [grunts]
Wow, that is not a good sign.
[yells]
[NOPHT] I expected a beast
to put up a better fight.
Completely insane.
[RHANTOLK]
Are you talking about the beast?
Or perhaps...?
[CHTHOLLY] Next Episode:
slight light, slight hope.