A‐ahh...
I... right hand... failure.
It's because of the canine.
Maturation and environment
were factors,
but it was lax with its studies.
[THUGS]
Hehe...
[THUG 3]
Hey little lady.
You a college student?
[GIRL]
Mm‐mm!
[THUG 1]
No? Really?
You work around here?
Ah, come on. It's okay.
We just wanna talk to ya.
[GIRL]
I'm sorry. Excuse me please.
[THUG 2]
Aw, now what's the big hurry.
You're not leavin' yet are ya?
Yeah. Dontcha wanna
have some fun?!
[GIRL] Ah!
Just relax‐
Urk! Ugh!
[Punching]
[THUG 2]
Hey what do you think you're‐
Gah!
Ugh!
I'll walk you.
Ahh...
Ugh...
[Grunt]
[GIRL]
AAAAHH!!
Think you can just
walk away fancy pants?!
Uhhh...
[THUGS]
Heh, heh, heh...
I don't think my stomach
can hold all four of you.
Your stomach?
[Swishing]
Seems two swings was
more force than necessary.
[GIRL]
Aaaahh!!
[Swish]
I should probably change
my appearance as well.
[HAND]
I take it you don't feel
the need to go to the
police anymore?
[SHINICHI]
Uh‐huh. I think I realized
that if I ran into another one
of you parasite things...
without you I'd be a
pretty easy target to kill.
A very wise decision.
[SHINICHI]
You know, I should probably
give you a name.
No thanks. I do not have
the needs of human beings.
Nor am I your pet.
Well I need to
call you something,
I can't just call you
"you" or "righty".
In that case...
you can call me Migi.
What? Migi?
Well sure. It means
the same thing,
but doesn't sound
nearly as silly.
Hmm... Well I'm not so sure
if I'd say that...
[MIGI]
Well, you're the one
who wanted a name.
I see no need for them anyway.
[Ball bouncing]
[Grunt]
Nice shot!
Whoo!
He's got some
nice moves.
Huh? Well... I...
Shinichi!
Huh?
Murano here says that
she'll totally forgive you
if you manage to
make another shot!
What are you doing Yuko?
&lt;Yuko chuckles&gt;
Uhh...
Hm...
Ow, hey!
Hmph!
What's his problem?
[Grunt]
Five seconds left!
Welp! Here goes nothing!
Aah!
Ha ha ha!
Uh... oh!
[Softly]
Thank you, Migi.
Pretty good, eh, Murano?
Uh‐huh...
Piece‐a‐shit, Shinichi...
Oh!
Oh, look at the time,
I gotta go!
Uh...
[SHINICHI] Um...
I'm sorry.
I really wasn't trying to
grab you like that yesterday.
It's just... My hand just
sorta went off on it's own...
and anyway...
I'm really sorry!
Well I'm glad you know
what you did was wrong.
Yes, yes it was!
It was so very wrong!
Well maybe I can find it in
my heart to forgive you
if you treat me to
pancakes next Sunday.
But hear this!
If you ever pull any crap
like that again you're dead!
No, no of course.
I won't, I promise.
Hehehe...
Okay then.
I'm holding you to it.
Hah...
[Shinichi screams]
Hmm?
Everything's just fine,
don't worry!
It's all good.
[Migi groans]
Ahh... [Exhales]
[SATOMI]
Um... Shinichi?
Huh?
You are... you ARE
Shinichi Izumi...
aren't you?
Well yeah...
Yeah of course I am!
What are you talking about?
[Chuckle]
See ya!
Are you crazy, what do you
think you're doing, man?!
I was just curious about your
human mating behavior.
I could sense you wanted to mate
with that female, correct?
Huh?!
No, no I did not want to
"mate" with her!
[NAGAI]
Shinichi!
Huh?
Come outside with me.
Now.
So why are you in there
talking to yourself,
ya practicing your
pickup lines? Huh?!
Uh, well...
I should probably
go get changed...
Hold it! I've had my
eye on Murano
since we were both
in middle school.
Oh yeah?
Is that so...?
You stay away from her.
Eh... Haha...
Come on, I don't want any‐
Ugh!
Aahh.. God...
What's your deal man?
[Grunt]
Ah!
Uuhh...
Gaahh...
Come on, get up!
You too much of a wuss
to fight back?
Come here!
[SHINICHI]
I can't...
If Migi gets involved,
this guy is gonna get
seriously messed up.
Ugh! Gah...
You're even weaker
than I thought you'd be!
Don't do it.
[Gasp] Ah!
Ugh!
Take it easy, you need to
hold back you idiot!
An "idiot"?
That word is to be used
when addressing a being
of lower intelligence.
[SHINICHI]
You didn't kill him,
did you?
He'll be just fine.
[NAGAI]
Ughh...
Ahhh...
Huh?!
Ooh! Aah!
[MIGI]
I'm detecting urine in
your bladder.
It isn't healthy to suppress
your excretory functions
in this manner.
[MIGI]
Shinichi.
Jesus, Seriously?!
I told you not to talk
whenever there's people around!
[MIGI]
Please hold still.
I'm going to try to make
your sex organ erect.
The hell you are!
Huh?
Huh? Ah!
No, no, no! Stop that!
I cannot believe you!
Uuh?
[MIGI]
Shinichi. That's cold.
[SHINICHI]
Be... quiet...
[MIGI]
If you do not wash properly,
dermatophytes will propagate,
causing such maladies
as jock itch‐
[SHINICHI]
I said shut up!
Dude, it's kinda hard
for me to pee
next to a guy
talkin' to his pecker.
Ah‐ahh! Uhh...
[School bell ringing]
[SHINICHI]
The "Mincemeat Murders"?
Yeah. From what I've heard,
it seems that they've been
happening all over the world.
The victims are literally
torn to pieces.
The police have been
trying to keep it quiet,
but some really graphic videos
have been showing up online.
What about the killer?
Still out there somewhere...
The thing is...
there's no way one person
could commit so many murders
all over the world at
the same time, right?
There has to be more people
involved in this,
like some kind of
crazy cult or something.
[SHINICHI]
Well, what does your
brother say about it?
He's a detective,
isn't he?
Yeah, well...
I asked him about it
the other day,
but he won't tell me
anything right now...
Which hopefully means that
the cops and the government
are already working on it
and trying to figure out
a way to solve this thing.
[SHINICHI]
So then, I guess this means
that more of your kind
are out there, huh?
[MIGI]
Most certainly.
When we ran into that canine
I learned something.
It would seem that those
inhabiting dogs only eat dogs.
While those who inhabit humans
will thus only eat humans.
Essentially, we are
cannibalistic.
What are you thinking,
Shinichi?
Should we really
stay quiet about this?
What exactly do you
mean by "stay quiet"?
We can't let them
run wild.
They're killing people
left and right.
What do you mean,
"run wild"?
Don't you get it?!
Only WE know what
they really are!
At this rate, there
will be more and more
victims every day.
Which is why...
"Which is why" what?
If I take you to 'em...
They can research you...
And learn what you are...
I don't understand.
Your logic's a bit difficult
for me to follow.
My kind are simply
feeding to stay alive
and nothing more.
It's natural for
life forms to feed
on other life forms.
You just find it unpleasant
that it's your own kind
that is being eaten.
Well yeah of course!
Human life is a
precious thing, isn't it?
I don't know.
I can tell you that
I value my own life.
Although I've never really
considered any other life form
to be all that valuable.
Yeah... bet you haven't.
'Cause you seem to be more like
an animal or an insect.
Shinichi...
is that an attempt
to be insulting?
Understand this.
If you were to take action
in any way that would be
harmful to me,
I would have no choice
but to do everything in
my power to stop you.
Uh‐huh...
Your survival depends on me.
You're just a parasite.
I WILL protect your life.
Although... you don't
necessarily need to
be able to speak.
Ah!
And then...
you don't really need
to be able to see
or hear either.
A‐ah...
Well... Looks like
someone's terrified.
Perhaps you should maybe
take a little rest.
[SHINICHI]
You're a demon...
[MIGI]
Shinichi, I have done some
research into the concept of
these "demons" you speak of.
And I would say that humans
are the life forms most
closely resembling them.
Humans tend to kill and
eat a multitude of
different life forms,
while my kind simply eats
only one or two.
We're quite frugal and
efficient in comparison.
Oh, whatever.
I'm not listening.
[SHINICHI]
People out there
are being killed.
And I'm the only one
who truly knows
what the killers are.
Mincemeat...
[B]
Hmm... Such a shallow breed.
They grind cows
and pigs into feed,
and then act so surprised
when it happens to them.
Hmm?
Well now...
Isn't this unusual.
It's one of my own.
[MIGI]
Shinichi.
One's coming this way.
Huh?
It's one of my kind.
It's somewhere over in
the crowd to our left.
There are too many people for
me to identify the individual,
but I'm certain that
one's there.
We need to fall back.
A single misstep now,
and it could mean another
fight to the death.
Walk faster.
It's getting closer.
Maybe it wants us to join
your little cannibal club.
[MIGI]
Shinichi! Where do you
think you're going?
It's forty meters away,
right behind you.
And it's gaining on us.
[SHINICHI]
I'm going to meet him.
I want to look this murderer
right in the eye.
[MIGI]
Don't be so foolish.
You'll get yourself killed.
[SHINICHI]
Then I guess you'll just
have to protect me.
[MIGI]
This is different.
We won't be up against
a dog this time.
No one will be able
to see us back here.
[MIGI]
I have much to learn
about the human mind.
You seem to be completely
numb to fear right now.
Tell me. Why is that?
A lot of people have
been killed since
these murders began.
If I don't do something,
Murano could be one of them.
I know you think
that I shouldn't do
anything about it.
That I should let these
things go on killing
people, but I can't!
I've got to fight!
Fight for humanity!
For humanity then...
I see.
And I'm going to need
your strength to do it.
I need your help.
Migi please...
Five meters.
Ah!
Uhh...
Now I see...
So this is the reason
you were running away.
[Nervous breathing]
Your host's brain is still
completely intact and
functional.
A rather dangerous situation
wouldn't you say?
Shut the hell up,
you monster!
Excuse me?
Stop right there!
If you attack this human,
I will be forced to
retaliate and destroy you.
Take it easy.
I understand.
I can appreciate where
you're coming from.
But you must realize...
you do have the option of
simply moving over to me.
A transfer?
I don't think relocation's
possible at this point.
What's that?
Looks like you still
have a lot to learn.
Relocating from
a mere appendage
to a more complex structure
would indeed be impossible.
That said... moving from
one arm to other is simple.
Huh!
Huh?
Well then?
I've created a location
for you to join me.
You should fit quite nicely.
Well? What are you waiting for,
it's time to transfer.
Once we inhabit the same host,
we'll both become more powerful!
What's the matter?
It's simple:
Kill your human and
relocate over here.
I'm losing a lot of
valuable blood.
If the two of us
manage this body
at the same time...
We could live upwards of
one hundred and forty years.
[Nervous breathing]
U‐uh... Migi...
You're wasting time.
But you will have
no choice in the matter
if your host no longer
has a head.
Uhhh!
Wh‐why would you do
such a thing?
What the...
what the hell is
wrong with you,
do you realize
what you've done?
My body...
I need my body...
I need my body to survive...
[Gasping]
[SHINICHI]
Migi...
Migi did you just save my life?
[MIGI]
I was simply unsure
if such a relocation
was possible to achieve.
The only life I consider
important is my own,
so I chose the safest option.
Very tired. I must sleep now.
[B]
My body...
I need my body...
I need my body to survive...
[SHINICHI]
I'm not sure how to take this.
Migi put my life over
one of his own kind.
Maybe he was only concerned
with saving himself,
but still...
[Whispering]
Migi... you awake?
Mmmm! So good!
Mmmm!
Hmm...
[SATOMI]
You know, if you're not enjoying
yourself you could say so.
Uh, no no it's really great!
Mmm‐mmm! Delicious!
Yeah, I am so not
buying that...
Hehehe...
Hahaha...
[Both laughing]
[SATOMI]
My parents are pretty strict
about me leaving the house
nowadays.
[SHINICHI]
Huh? Why's that?
[SATOMI]
Well, because of everything
that's been going on.
You know, the Mincemeat Murders.
[SHINICHI] Oh, right...
[SATOMI] It's just awful.
I mean, they're getting
cut to pieces?
What's wrong with people?
[SHINICHI]
Yeah...
Man, if she ever
found out about Migi,
she would completely
freak out for sure.
Um, is something wrong?
Hey Murano...
you like animals,
don't you?
Mm‐hm! Yeah of course.
Except worms,
they're creepy.
Aah! Ugh!
Are you okay?
Uh‐huh...
[SATOMI]
Hey! Come over here!
Uh?
C'mon c'mon.
I wanna play in the sandbox!
Meow!
[Boys laughing]
[Boy 1] Aw crap...
[Boy 2]
Dude, you suck.
It's my turn.
[Grunt]
[Boy 1]
Air ball! Heh, heh!
That's horrible...
[Boy 2]
Whatever, man.
Got closer than you.
Let's go.
I cannot watch this...
Yeah, who could?
Huh?
Hehe... Huh?
[Boy 3]
Who's this clown?
Hey you guys.
You really need to cut it out.
Huh?!
Meow...
Oh, wow...
Meow!
Aw c'mon, we're just
playing around, man!
Yeah, try mindin'
your own business?
It is a living breathing thing.
Not a toy for you to play with.
It's alive just like you.
Tsk!
Loser!
Seriously dude?
[Guy 3]
What a tool.
Hm...
Hehe...
Hmph!
Look out!
Whoa!
Uhh!
I will eat you alive.
Aahh! Ooh!
Let's go.
Uh... O‐okay.
[SHINICHI]
Maybe Migi was right about us.
Maybe human beings
aren't so sacred.
Maybe... maybe we're
the demons after all.
Uhh!
Huh...
Uh...
Hm...
Hehe...
Oh!
Hey, Shinichi?
Yeah?
You ARE...
Shinichi Izumi...
aren't you?
Yeah.
Of course I am.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Symposium"