Shinichi, your eyes...
your eyes have no tears.
[SHINICHI]
Goodbye... Murano...
[MIGI]
Shinichi, I was
unsure earlier about
what would happen.
[SHINICHI]
This was for the best, right?
I mean, if that guy had
been watching us again,
he'd probably start
going after Murano next.
[MIGI]
"That guy"?
Yeah...
Y'know the man from before...
He was watching me again
this afternoon, too.
Why didn't you
say so sooner?
'Cause you would've
tried to kill him.
[MIGI]
Well, I've changed my
thinking on that matter.
His investigation of
you would appear to
be ongoing, correct?
If the same person is
continuing to operate
despite us having
discovered him,
we could actually be
facing several enemies.
We may as well track down
everyone involved in this
investigation and then‐
Kill them all, right?
No...
In fact, I've noticed
just how adverse a
reaction you have
when it comes to the
idea of killing
other humans.
And that means,
we will have to
work together.
Oh's that so?
Therefore, we should
set aside the idea of
killing him for now.
Instead, we should
investigate him.
How exactly?
We will call in an ally
and ask for help.
An ally, huh...?
But where in the world
would we ever find one?
Oh!
[SHINICHI]
Sorry for making you
come here.
And getting you involved
in all this, of course.
What are you talking about?
You two can count on us.
You're the only ones
in the same boat we are!
We have to help
each other out y'know!
I know, but...
but you kinda already helped
me out enough already...
[PARASITE]
You got that right!
You totally owe us...!
This is a huge pain for us!
[UDA]
[Muffled struggling]
That was not me just now.
Right.
[PARASITE]
Seriously. I get it.
But wouldn't it be better
just to kill the guy?
[UDA]
No, we can't.
It's not that easy, all right?
Anyway, do you have any idea
who might be behind all this?
[SHINICHI]
Actually, I think we do.
[MIGI]
Assuming the enemy isn't
some organization...
we do have a guess.
Okay, let's say we're
gonna just try to catch him
instead of kill him.
You at least know what
he looks like, right?
[MIGI]
Yes, I remember him well.
Like this.
Okay... I got it.
[Muffled struggling]
[UDA]
For now, I think we're
going to stay
in the hotel over by
the train station.
[SHINICHI]
Right. Okay.
Oh, by the way.
About this guy's name...
we decided "Parasite"
was too confusing
because they use that
on TV and everywhere...
so I've decided to
call him "Joe".
[JOE]
He so desperately needs
a friend you guys.
Hehe.
Guh. I do not get it with
all the friggin' names.
[MIGI]
I agree.
Names are totally unimportant.
[Foot tapping]
You look like
you're exhausted.
You should really
go see a doctor.
Hm. I did go see
a doctor... Look!
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Yeah, well, they wouldn't
believe me anyway.
Someone's hand
stretching out
and attacking me?
But it did happen,
and I did get hurt...
I mean this is real,
isn't it...?!
Isn't it?
Please calm yourself down.
Eh... Sigh...
Believe it or not,
I've calmed down quite a bit...
And I've taken time to think
about what happened back there.
As in, what the hell
was that... thing?
I haven't come up
with anything.
Well nothing that makes
any sorta sense at least.
I'll pay you for all the work
you've done up until now...
But your job's over.
Over? But we've just barely
scratched the surface...?
I mean come on here...
How am I supposed to deal
with all this crazy stuff?
I... I at least have to
figure out what that thing was!
Asking me to believe
your story is far
more unreasonable.
I guess I...
Hold on!
Wait a second!
You mentioned something
to me about Shinichi Izumi's
hand before, didn't you.
Oh?
You did...!
You definitely did!
So then you...
You already knew about it!
You knew!
That's the whole reason you
asked me to investigate him
in the first place!
Do you know what that
monster actually is...?
Look, you gotta tell me
what's going on here lady!
Would you stop this
foolishness? We're done.
Hey! I can't just
walk away from this‐
[Falling on floor]
Ah... Ow...
Ugh... Aww..
Hmph.
This would seem to be as far
as I can go using the humans.
Ultimately, very little
was accomplished.
Perhaps I should get rid
of that investigator.
[Small chuckles]
Huh?
[Door closing]
[Small chuckles]
Hahaha...
Was I really laughing
just now...?
That's the first time
I've ever laughed without
making myself do so.
But when I saw how panicked
that man looked...
Heh!
I completely forgot about
my facial expressions.
Hehehe...
Hahaha...
[Maniacal laughter]
[Baby crying]
Sigh...
Already asleep, huh?
[Glug]
Ahh...
[Door opens]
Hm?
[YOKO]
Ahh! What a day.
Oh, well, well.
Enjoying yourself, I see.
Want some?
No, I'll pass.
Sigh...
Hm?
You've had it pretty rough
lately, haven't you?
What?
You've been having
bad dreams...
You cry out
in your sleep.
And now you've
gotten yourself hurt.
Don't worry.
It's no big deal.
So... is this job that
you've been working on
really just a
background check?
Do what?
What're you talking about?
I'm just saying
that nothing good
is going to come from
getting involved in...
in things that you
don't belong, that's all.
So now you're thirsty
all of a sudden?
If this job gets
too dangerous...
well then, isn't that
what the cops are for.
I just don't want
anything to happen to you.
I don't want you getting
in over your head.
[Glass clink]
Okay?
What you don't think
I'm cut out for this, ugh...
No. Maybe not this one.
Jesus hon, thanks for
the vote of confidence.
I gotta do this...
I gotta show the
whole goddamn world!
[SHINICHI]
The parasites
transmit signals...
Those transmissions
allow them to sense
the others of their kind
that're located nearby.
They can't talk to each other
like they're on the phone
or anything,
but if they agree on a kind of
"call sign" beforehand,
they're able to exchange
simple messages.
[MIGI]
Shinichi.
They've found him.
[SHINICHI]
Got it.
[MIGI]
We'll meet him at
the next corner.
[SHINICHI]
Understood.
Huh?
Huh? Ah!
Glad you came...
I didn't think
you'd show up.
Gah!
[Muffled]
Please don't say anything.
Now get in.
Who's he? What're you guys
planning to do to me?
Look, we don't intend to
cause you any harm...
We're just going someplace
where we can talk in private.
[Nervous sounds]
[SHINICHI]
He doesn't need to be
so afraid of us...
[SHINICHI]
Honestly, there's so
much I want to ask you.
But first... I'd like you to
hear about our side of things.
Fine. Sure I'll
hear you out, okay.
But you gotta tell me
what's up with this guy.
There is something
wrong with his face!
He changed it a bit
so you wouldn't know
what he looks like.
Uh, y‐yeah...
Right... Please listen closely
to what I have to say to you...
My own life is
at stake right now.
O‐kay...
[SHINICHI]
And then...
I went through everything‐
all the way from when
Migi dug into my hand
right up to the present.
Naturally, he was pretty
shocked at first,
but the more he listened
to my story...
the calmer he seemed to become.
But, even though he had begun
to relax while I talked...
that skeptical look
never left his eyes.
[KURAMORI]
All right.
I get the gist of things.
I'm sure you know how crazy
this whole thing sounds...
Normally there's no way
I'd believe it...
but seeing as how there's
a whatever right here
in front of me...
I have to unfortunately
believe at least some of it.
So? What do you
want me to do?
I'm asking you
to keep this quiet.
Can you do that for us?
I understand your point but
according to your own account,
there are more of
these things out there.
Can we really just
stand by and do nothing?
Uh?
If you really do
care about humanity...
Then you...
you have an obligation
to come forward on this.
Even if they turn you into
some kind of experiment...
Even if it means sacrificing
yourself, you have to
think of civilization!
You have to think
of all of us!
Isn't that what it
means to be human?
What'd I say?
We should totally
take this guy out!
Agreed.
Uh! Ah!
Ahh!
Stop it!
[JOE]
Maybe you should
sacrifice yourself.
[MIGI]
I want you to listen
to me very closely.
If you have a right to live,
then we have that same right.
Granted, the concept of "rights"
may be uniquely human,
but in any case,
you need to understand
that we will do anything
to ensure our own survival.
And I will not allow him
to come forward
and be turned into
some kind of specimen.
If you're saying that will
make you our enemy...
I could kill you at
a moment's notice.
Aah!
[MIGI]
Take a good look at him.
He's a teenager,
still in high school.
From your perspective,
he's still a child, correct?
His mother was killed...
He's endured a great deal.
He has been forced to
step over a pile of corpses,
yet continues to try his
best to solve things.
I believe this is when you
humans are supposed to
experience compassion.
Would you be able to
endure all this?
[Crying]
[SHINICHI]
Migi doesn't really sound
like himself at all right now.
I'm sure he's just saying
that stuff to get a reaction
out of this guy, but still...
Okay listen...
I honestly do not
plan to kill you.
Run for it! Hurry!
Yeah... I know.
[MIGI]
I have one more question.
I want to know‐ who asked you
to investigate Shinichi?
Yeah right...
You know I can't say that.
What...!
Are you serious?
Are you really gonna
try and pull some self
righteous bullcrap now?
Well, we do already have a
pretty good idea who it is...
And to be perfectly blunt, your
client is actually a parasite.
Wait what?...!
That can't be right!
I believe he mentioned her
earlier, didn't he...?
She was the female teacher
who just disappeared from
his high school...
Ryoko Tamiya.
Who... Who's Tamiya?
She's already
changed her name,
but your client's name
could possibly sound similar.
Ryoko Tamiya...
Reiko Tamura... [Gasp]
Look I barely even
get the concept of
having stupid names,
but I coulda
figured that out.
If you decide to continue
digging deeper into this,
it will be your client
rather than us who kills you.
Son of a bitch...
[Phone buzzing]
[TAMURA]
Shinichi Izumi?
[SHINICHI]
Ah! It's you!
[MIGI]
To think, she got
in touch with you
right after we
suspected something...
[SHINICHI]
She wants to meet on the
roof of the university...
What do you think she's up to?
Right now, Ryoko Tamiya
is one hundred thirty
meters from us...
Which means she must be
somewhere beyond that building.
She went from high‐school
teacher to college professor...
Very ambitious.
[PROFESSOR]
Altruism is action undertaken
for the sole benefit of others.
It's the opposite of
self‐interest, and would seem
to have no benefit for oneself.
If anything, the action tends
help others while being
disadvantageous to the actor.
‐What a cutie.
‐Aw, so sweet!
While these actions may
not be surprising amongst
what can be interpreted
as altruistic behavior
has actually been reported
in several animal species.
Honeybees are an excellent
example of this,
they sacrifice themselves,
one after another,
to protect the hive if
a predator should appear.
While this could
just be instinct,
some actions would not seem
to preserve the species.
The prime illustration of
such a practice could
be identified...
as infanticide.
But why kill the offspring
of one's own species?
In recent years,
what's been discovered is...
something called the
"selfish gene" theory...
To put it in simple terms,
all animals are manipulated by
their own body's genetic code.
What's important is the self,
and the offspring
who inherit that DNA,
rather than the species
as a whole.
That being said...
Let's expand a bit further...
We can now justify all
altruistic behavior,
such as caring for others
in one's "pack,"
familial love, marital love
and even maternal love.
This premise would suggest
that love and compassion
don't actually exist.
Therefore, all behavior
that appears to be love
is really just behavior to aid
in transmitting one's own DNA.
To be sure, this theory is
not without its problems.
There have been countless
examples of animals helping
others completely unrelated
to them.
This includes like creatures
from unrelated DNA strains,
and even instances of
protecting those of a
different species altogether.
Which begs the question,
can a theory like this
fully encompass
the complexity or the depth
of the human consciousness?
For example, it's interesting
to consider whether human
efforts toward such issues
as environmental‐and‐natural
conservation are altruistic
or selfish at their core.
[TAMURA]
It's almost time.
Who holds a baby like that?
Yeah...
[Door creaks open]
[TAMURA]
I'm glad you came.
You look well.
Why'd you want us
to meet here?
I chose this place
because others of my
kind rarely come here.
Also, there was a lecture
I wanted to attend.
So it's true.
You are quite different
from before.
How did the two
of you combine...?
What really happened...?
I find it difficult to believe
it occurred without reason.
Uh...?!
So is that really...
your baby?
Yes. It is mine...
I haven't had it long, so I
haven't began working on it yet.
Working on it?
How so?
Your right hand...
"Migi," wasn't it...?
Shall we exchange
information again...?
For both our sakes.
[MIGI]
First, I'd like to confirm
it was you who hired the
private investigator.
Hm.
Didn't you think that doing so
might put you in
great danger as well?
I don't really
worry about it...
I know I can simply
assume another identity,
if it comes to that.
So what's the deal with
this Mayor Hirokawa?
Why would one of your kind
want to be mayor anyway?
I'm not entirely
sure myself...
And yet... I know that
we are still evolving.
We've learned that
recklessly slaughtering
human beings for food
is not a wise
option for us.
Going forward,
we're going to have
to think about...
how we can coexist
with humans.
"Coexist"?
Hideo Shimada said the same
thing, you saw what he did.
Couldn't it be said that,
in a way, humans and
their livestock coexist?
Now, that's not to say
you're equals...
But still, judging from
a pig's point of view,
humans are merely predators
that feed upon them.
Humans are so fond of
grandiose ideals.
You grasp onto the
notion that all life
on Earth is sacred,
yet you don't behave
in such a way.
I'll admit, there may
be a little truth
to some of the things
that you're saying.
But that being said...
There are reasons why I will
never be able to forgive you!
What happened to you?
You just don't really seem
to be like a normal human
being anymore...
I'm not sure how to put it...
[Grunt]
[Baby starts to cry]
Huh...
A mother and... child...
[Grunting]
I heard that your mother
went missing.
Uh...
Was she killed?
Ah...
[Heart beating]
[Gasping in pain]
[MIGI]
Shinichi, calm down!
[Labored breathing]
[Baby whiney]
Hahaha... I see!
So, one of us ate her.
Huh...
Ohh... Impressive...
It's like the air is
trembling around us...
I'm gonna kill you!
[Baby crying]
I think I'd lose
if I fought you now...
So, I'll have to use the
child to shield myself.
Ah!
[Baby crying]
Omigod look?!
It's that lady from class.
[TAMURA]
It seems human children are
more perceptive than adults.
Be quiet.
[Panting]
[SHINICHI]
That bitch...
Move it! Get outta my way!
[SHINICHI]
Goddamn humans...
[MIGI]
What's wrong, Shinichi?
You must settle yourself.
[SHINICHI]
She will pay...
Her day is gonna come!
So, I'll have to use the
child to shield myself.
I haven't had it long, so I
haven't began working on it yet.
[Panting]
[Out of breath]
[Woman]
Hello, young man.
Yes, you!
Huh?
Yes... Come on...
Come here...
I do reading.
Yes that's it...
You seem to be
full of suffering...
Let me see your hand.
Let's go.
[FORTUNE TELLER]
Left hand?
Hmmm...
I see you have a hole in
your heart now, don't you?
Huh?!
How did you...?
Oh, it's a very
large hole indeed.
So then how can I...
how can I close it?
See the person.
What?
You have to meet once again with
whomever created this hole...
You must meet with them
and have talk.
Then you have closure.
Yes... This individual is
the only one who can
heal your wounds.
There is no other way.
[Scary chuckle]
[Gasp]
Huh?
Too late for that,
I already killed her.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Something Wicked
This Way Comes"