[YOUNG WOMAN] (ah!)
I think I drank too much!
Well, I should
probably get going.
[YOUNG WOMAN]
(uh...) Now, hold on!
What's the big rush, huh?
Sit down.
Hey, y'know, you're a lot
cuter than Shiro said.
[KATO] You're embarrassing me.
(chuckles)
[YOUNG WOMAN] Ha‐ha, I mean it,
seriously.
Have you heard about
that hair thingy?
Hold still...
(laughs) Sorry about that!
I pulled out three by acci‐
(huh?)
No...
This is awkward.
(thwack!)
(bushes rustling)
It was the hair
that gave me away.
I could use some help.
I don't normally eat meat
containing alcohol.
(wet slurping)
(birds chirping)
(huh?) (gasps)
(breathy gurgles)
[KANA] (gasps)
[KANA] (whimpers)
(running)
(screams)
(whimpers)
(ah!)
(heroic music)
(horse whinnies)
(shwick!)
(huh?)
I owe you...
I owe you my life.
(birds chirping)
(sighs)
I can't believe he'd do
something like that.
How do Shinichi and I
seem similar to you?
I mean, whatever it is
you think you're sensing,
it could be some kind of
"wavelengths" being
broadcast
by dangerous jerks like him.
Don't tell me Shinichi...
Huh?
(footsteps)
[KANA] (ah!)
Nobody likes
being snuck up on.
Oh, sorry!
(sighs)
Look, if you really
want one of my hairs,
you can help yourself.
Oh, uh...
Okay, thank you.
[SHINICHI] You happy now?
[KANA] (ah!)
Oh...
[KANA] Wait up!
Hey, I remember you warned me
before about hanging around
Shimada.
Does that mean you already knew
about what he was capable of
from the start?
No, I... I didn't.
(chuckles) I guess not.
I mean who would be friends
with a mass murderer, right?
[KANA]
What's with the serious look?
[SHINICHI]
She has a special gift.
Maybe I could go ahead
and tell her everything.
No, I shouldn't,
not while Migi's still awake.
[MIGI] Shinichi,
I know what you're thinking.
But don't do it.
That female is no ally of mine.
Nor is she an ally of yours.
Your name is Kana, isn't it?
Huh? Yeah, yeah that's right!
[SHINICHI] You said that you
have some strange telepathic
ability to sense my presence,
but even if you feel like
I'm close by,
you should not try
to approach me.
[KANA] Why not?
[SHINICHI] Because you might run
into something else instead.
[KANA] What? Like a monster?
[SHINICHI] Yeah.
Now why would you say that?
I mean, you're a normal human
being, aren't you, Shinichi?
Yeah, of course
I'm a normal human.
Hmm... Well, if my senses do
happen to point me in the
direction of someone,
I already know
what it is I need to do.
I'll pluck out a hair to see
if they're safe or not.
No, Kana! You cannot do that!
[KANA] (soft gasp)
You okay?
Ah, I'm sorry.
It's just really dangerous,
you know.
Does that mean
you're worried about me?
That makes me kinda happy.
[MIGI] Shinichi...
I need to talk to you.
Ah, I have to get going!
I'm really sorry.
See ya.
[KANA] Huh?
[KANA] Oh, hello there.
Um, hello.
[MIGI] Shinichi, I don't want
you to speak to that
person again.
[SHINICHI] I can't do that.
You know if I just
walk away from her,
then eventually she's
gonna get into trouble.
Perhaps, but I believe
the way you talk to her
has revealed
more than enough already.
I'll be careful.
[MIGI] I hope so.
I, um... I know it's strange
to ask you this out of
the blue, but...
[KANA] Ask me what?
Do you... think that Shinichi's
been acting a little
different lately?
I've actually only
met him a few times.
I'm not so sure if I would
really be a fair judge.
I mean when you first met him
versus right now.
Did you two have a fight?
You like him, right?
I can kinda tell.
Look, he's just different
somehow, okay?
Not so much when we're talking,
but when...
Mm‐hmm...
I... I mean,
he did save my life!
He saved your life?!
So you mean you have dreams
like that, too?
Huh? Dreams?
Ah! Uh...
I guess I just don't see it.
I get the feeling he's been
this way all along, you know?
He's got this kind of
intensity about him.
[KANA] Well, if you don't
stop acting so mopey,
then you're gonna
lose him for sure.
Looks like I might
still have a chance!
[MAN]
I'll be back in ten minutes.
Understood, but, uh...
Couldn't you have worn
something a bit more...
normal looking?
It'll just get dirty.
(exhales)
What do you want?
How many are inside?
Are you kidding me?
You some kinda moron?
Get outta here
before you get hurt.
Ah, of course, you yakuza
are quite aggressive.
(grr...)
Okay, Short Shorts,
all these new anti‐gang laws
are cute and all,
but it won't keep you from
getting your ASS BEAT, YOU
UNDERSTAND?! (umphf!)
[YAKUZA]
Hey! Who the hell are you?!
[BOTH] (huh?)
(thwack)
[YAKUZA] (screams)
We got company!
[ALL] (huh?)
[YAKUZA] (ah!) (nervous sounds)
(grr...)
(hyah!)
(ungh!)
(umpf!)
(aahhh...)
(nervous whimpers)
(urk!)
(kyah!) (ungh...)
(gaahhh!)
(nervous sounds)
What's wrong?
Let's go.
(grr...)
(kyah!)
(umphf)
(gasps) (ungh!)
[YAKUZA] (hungh!)
[MAN] That's one.
[YAKUZA]
Damn you! You're a dead man!
(snap!)
[YAKUZA] (gasps)
(aarrgh!)
(waahhh!)
Two...
(omphf!)
Heh, gotcha.
[YAKUZA] That's it asshole.
That makes three.
What?! This guy's not dead?!
[YAKUZA] Holy shit!
[MAN] They managed three hits.
I guess that's about right.
What the hell?!
(shwick!)
What's this all about, man?
It's an experiment.
We wanted to determine exactly
how successful we would be
against a group heavily armed
with weapons.
[YAKUZA] No, please!
[MAN] My god what the hell
happened over there?
That guy,
his head got bashed in!
I'm pretty sure
I heard some gunshots.
Yeah, me too!
[ALL] (gasps)
(nervous reactions)
Hey, he's getting away!
[MAN] Hey, get back here!
What the...
Where'd he go?
He was right in front of us.
Let's get outta here.
I don't want to get in the
middle of some damn gang war.
[MAN] Maybe you're right.
But don't you think we should
at least call the cops
or somethin'?
[MAN] Nah, I'm sure
somebody already did.
(gate squeaks)
What is it?
[DRIVER] Nothing. It's just,
you're quite different
from before.
[YUKO] Mass murder at
a gang headquarters...
It says 22 people
were massacred,
every single
yakuza member there.
That's crazy.
It's like it keeps getting worse
out there every single day.
Yeah...
[SHINICHI] Was that a parasite?
No, they wouldn't kill like
that unless they needed
to feed.
The Metropolitan Police
Department has just held an
emergency press conference.
They made the announcement that
they will soon be releasing
security camera footage
of a male suspect fleeing
the scene.
That may have been a bit much.
It was a very successful
exercise. Very.
[SATOMI] Shinichi, hey!
I'm glad you're here.
Thanks for coming.
Um‐hmm. Thank you for asking me
to come out today, kind sir.
(laughing)
What d'ya wanna do?
I dunno, wanna go watch
a movie or something?
Sure!
[SATOMI] I don't know about you,
but I still have nightmares
about that day sometimes.
Even after I know I'm awake,
I just can't stop myself
from shaking.
Does that ever happen to you,
Shinichi?
Yeah, sometimes.
But by the end of the morning,
I'm usually okay.
You're lucky.
Unfortunately, my dreams are
always so... disturbing
I can't get them out of my head.
Well, actually, a friend told
me something one time.
He said it helps to think of
people like cows and pigs.
When you look at it that way,
you can kinda see that people
are eating chopped‐up animals
all the time,
So it's natural. There's really
nothing for you to be afraid of.
That's kinda strange...
What kind of person
would say that?
Ah... Hmm...
No one like you've ever met.
Well, maybe it's
because of this friend...
that you've changed so much.
No, it's not that...
I don't think so.
Look, I'm sorry!
I don't mean anything bad,
it's just you're different,
that's all.
I never know which Shinichi's
gonna show up.
It was that trip.
Ever since he got back,
he hasn't been the same.
Um, Shinichi...
When your dad got hurt while on
vacation, and then, you went‐
(chair sliding on floor)
(gasps)
Let's get going.
I guess I shouldn't have
asked him about it.
(puppy barking)
[SAMOTI] (giggles)
[SATOMI] Oh, how cute!
Come here, little guy!
(puppy whining)
(dog panting)
(ah!)
(dog barking)
[SATMOI] Wha?!
(puppy whining)
Is that your mama?
Must be.
[SATOMI] Maybe they're strays.
(puppy barking)
Oh, I guess not.
She has a collar.
[SATOMI] (huh?) Shinichi?
[SHINICHI] What a great day.
It's not even that
cold out here.
(ha!)
You sound just like an old man!
Old man? Aw, c'mon.
[LITTLE BOY] Mommy! (crying)
[BOTH] (huh?)
Hey, Mommy, come back!
Wait for me, Mommy! (crying)
[MOM] Hey, come on. Let's go.
Come on.
[LITTLE BOY] (crying)
Mommy, you're stupid!
You're stupid!
[MOM] (uh!)
Hey, now...
[LITTLE BOY] (louder crying)
There's no need to get ugly.
[LITTLE BOY] I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
Excuse me?
How can you say that to me?
[LITTLE BOY] (continues sobbing)
I hope you die, Mommy!
(grrr!)
[SHINICHI] (gasps) (ungh...)
[LITTLE BOY] (quiet whimpers)
(sighs) Come on, let's go.
[SHINICHI] (gasping for breath)
What's wrong?!
[SHINICHI] A hole...
There's a hole!
A hole?
Uh, I, uh...
[SATOMI] What's going on?
Are you okay?
(deep breath) It was really
hard to breathe all of a sudden.
Maybe I am old.
Oh, cut it out! Now you're just
being pathetic, grandpa!
(laughs) Okay...
[SHINICHI] Sometimes...
it's like my body
is being torn apart.
But then,
the sensation just goes away.
That's when I feel like
a part of Migi really has
merged with me.
But... I really do like Murano.
I care about her
more than anything.
And there's one thing that
I'm absolutely sure of:
That feeling...
it comes from MY heart.
When I'm with her,
it makes me wish
Migi would just...
stay asleep.
Stay asleep... forever.
(soft gasp)
(sighs)
I'll see ya.
[SATOMI] (small chuckle)
(sighs)
[SATOMI] You... you really are
Shinichi Izumi, right?
[SATOMI] If only we had...
If only we had gotten closer
to each other sooner.
If that were the case...
I could truly believe
without any doubt in my heart...
that you really are Shinichi.
I'm such an idiot.
I should've known
from the beginning.
But!
(phone ringing)
[MIGI] Why are you making
the effort to see her?
[SHINICHI] She said it's the
last favor she'll ever ask.
So how could I ignore her?
[MIGI] I do not really
understand that.
[SHINICHI] Guess I got here
a bit too early.
One of my kind is nearby.
[SHINICHI] (ah!)
Wait, not just one of them,
but three. No, five.
Well, are there three
or are there five?!
They're over there.
[PA]
We, each and every one of us,
must alter our way of thinking.
[MIGI] They've noticed us.
[PA] As it now stands,
the topic of global
environmental conservation
[MIGI] But they still
haven't made a move.
[PA] is merely viewed
as a fad or pure fashion.
Y'know something, Migi?
You and I may be the weirdest
crime‐fighting duo ever.
[MIGI] Shinichi...
They're currently about
sixty meters away.
Eight of them in total.
Two are down low...
And six are elevated...
Still no aggression.
(gasps)
[PA]
Could you give up your vehicle
to prevent just
an ounce of pollution?
Completely reversing the course
of our daily lives
is next to impossible.
But if we choose to do nothing,
All six up there...
[PA] our entire planet
is in eminent danger.
They're all parasites?
[MIGI] And the two below.
[MIGI] At this distance it
would be difficult for them
to identify us,
but they might
if we make eye contact.
[PA] A popular approach is to
use scare tactics to try to
elicit results,
offering a terrifying glimpse
into of a dismal future,
threatening that
we're doomed to fail.
(gasps) Did he see us?
No, no way, not with this crowd.
[MIGI] He saw us.
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
Your eyes met.
But they don't seem to be very
interested in us at this time.
Shinichi, now we've
seen what's going on,
I say we get out of here.
[SHINICHI] Yeah...
A parasite running for mayor?
What the hell are they up to?
[KANA] Hey, Shinichi!
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
[SHINICHI]
What are you doing here?!
Uh, yeah, well...
I just so happen to live
in this neighborhood.
And ya know, I'm the one
who asked you here.
Oh, right, of course you did.
[PA] But it's right here,
in front of you!
It's at the local level and not
with the national bureaucrats
that environmental issues can
start to be addressed...
[SHINICHI] This is bad...
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Kokoro"