[SHINICHI]
Not long ago, someone on Earth
had a passing thought...
(cracking)
(roar)
[WOMAN] (terrified whimpers)
(continued whimpers)
[MUFFLED VOICE] I have failed...
This is unfortunate.
What? What's unfortunate?
[MUFFLED VOICE] Be quiet.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
What a dream....
That was the worst
night's sleep...
(sizzling)
Did you find that
"worm" of yours?
My hand feels kinda numb.
[MOM] Well, probably because you
wrapped your headphone cord
around it last night.
Can I...
Can I just have toast.
No, sir! You need to eat
a proper breakfast.
Come on, gimme a break.
I had a rough night.
That's because you
stayed up too late.
Hm?
(gasps) (pain)
[DAD]
Relax, it's just a spider.
[MOM] Seriously, Shinichi,
when are you gonna get over
this silly fear of bugs?
[NEWSCAST] At the latest
meeting of the OECD...
[MAN] At... the... latest...
meeting of the O‐E‐C‐D...
[LITTLE GIRL]
Daddy! Where's Mommy?
I need something to eat.
[MAN] (mimicking)
Daddy! Where's Mommy?
I need something to eat.
(slurping noise)
[SATOMI] (giggles)
Hi‐yaa!
(waah!) Murano?!
Ah, don't act surprised.
What do you mean?
Come on, you obviously knew
I was sneaking up behind you.
Ah, no, I didn't!
Huh?
Uh...
(WAAHHH!) Oh my God, oh crap!
I'm so sorry!
[SATOMI] (hmpf!)
I didn't mean to, I swear.
I mean I‐ (ungh!)
[SATOMI] Real nice, Shinichi.
Real nice!
[YUKO] What the heck
were you thinking?
[SHINICHI] Yuko...
I don't know what's
wrong with me.
Ah man, I am off today...
S'there a problem
with your hand?
[SHINICHI] Uh... no.
It's fine.
(sleepy breathing)
(snoring)
(gnuhng) (violent cough)
(waah!)
What the...?!
(tapping)
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
[SHINICHI] (ungh)
What the hell is going on?!
[SHINICHI] (nngh)
(knock on door)
[DAD] Shinichi!
Is everything alright?!
Help me!
What the hell is
going on in here?
[MOM] (gasps)
[MOM]
What are you doing to your arm?
There's...
There's something in it!
A worm or something!
A what?!
[MOM] A worm?
(heavy sigh)
Ah, you've gotta be kidding me.
I'm telling you the truth!
It's like it burrowed a hole
right into my arm!
Uh‐huh...
Okay, son, let's have
a look at it then.
[SHINICHI]
Look! It's right... Huh?
Okay, son, please don't tell me
that you are on drugs.
[SHINICHI]
No, no, I'm not! I swear!
(giggles) Honestly, sweetie,
don't scare us like that.
That's weird...
Doesn't even hurt or anything.
[SHINICHI] It felt so real.
I couldn't have just imagined
the whole thing, right?
[YUKO] Shinichi!
[SHINICHI] Hm?
[TEACHER] Hmm...
[SHINICHI]Uh‐ ah‐
Hmm?
[SHINICHI] Huh?
My lecture not riveting
enough for ya?
I think you're aware that
the use of cell phones
is not permitted
during class hours.
[SHINICHI] I thought I
turned it off, and... and I...
Yes?
[SHINICHI] Sorry, sir.
[TEACHER] (hmpf)
[YUKO] (sighs)
[SHINICHI] Huh?
Uh, Murano,
about this morning...
[YUKO] Looks like she's
still pretty pissed off.
Okay, look, because you're
my friend and I'm such
a wonderful person,
I'll go and apologize for you.
[SHINICHI] Really? Thanks, Yuko.
But first you have to
tell me if you're okay.
Because well...
you don't look so good.
[SHINICHI] Yeah...
I don't really
feel so good either.
I think I'm gonna ask the
teacher if maybe I can go home.
[SHINICHI]
There's no way my hand could
just move on its own could it?
I mean, after that
thing from last night,
I don't know what to think.
(car honking)
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
[LITTLE GIRL] (giggling)
(car horn)
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
(brakes screeching)
(broken car horn)
(gasps)
[LITTLE GIRL] (loud crying)
[MOM] (panicked gasp)
Oh, my God,
thank goodness you're okay!
(door opening)
(hmm?)
Is that Shinichi?
Well, he's home early.
(door slamming)
(heavy, panicked breathing)
I don't know how the hell
you got in there... (whimpers)
...but you're coming out!
(gasps)
(whimpering)
How very unfortunate.
(waah!)
I... right hand... failure.
F‐failure?
What did you do to my hand?
I have... I have eaten it. Gone.
(nervous laughter)
[SHINICHI] (soft whimpers)
I am, uh...
new to talking your language.
You must teach me, Shinichi.
(gasps)
Just what are you?
So tired. I sleep now.
Huh?! Wait a minute!
You've got to answer
some questions first!
Hey! Come on, wake up!
(knock on door)
[MOM] Shinichi?
Is everything all right?
Hello? Shinichi?
[SHINICHI] No! Don't come in!
[MOM] (gasps)
[SHINICHI] I'm fine...
Everything's fine!
[MOM] (uh...)
(grrr...)
Awww....
How can I even search
for something like this?
I mean who ever heard of
something like this
ever happening
to anyone before?
[MOM]
Shinichi! Dinner's ready!
[MOM] I got a call from
the school today.
They said you left early.
[DAD]
Oh yeah? Something happen?
Nothing much.
Just felt a little sick,
that's all.
[MOM] Anything serious?
[SHINHICHI] Nah.
Oh? You want seconds?
You must feel better.
So you don't feel well, but you
still have an appetite, huh?
Well, I'm feeling better now.
What's the big deal?
I can't tell Mom and Dad
about this...
They'll think I'm crazy.
[DRUNK]
I love you, love yooou!
Ah, face.
Oh, God...
Ha! Too many drinky drinks!
Huh?
(screams)
[WOMAN] Nakamura! You left your
laundry outside in the rai...
(screams)
Actually...
I can't tell anyone about this.
If I went to the police,
they'd probably put me away
for the rest of my life.
And if I went to a doctor,
I'd just end up being
their freakshow.
Then everyone would know.
I don't know what to do.
Hey.
Wake up.
(birds tweeting)
(uhmm...)
Is it morning?
Yes, it is...
It's morning and I'm awake!
(big sigh)
I'm still having a nightmare.
What are you doing?
As you can see.
I'm studying.
I see you can
speak pretty well now.
So, what are you?
Are you an alien or something?
An alien?
What's an alien?
[SHINICHI]
Is that wormy thing what you're
really supposed to look like?
[HAND] I can't help but notice
that none of your biology texts
seem to have anything about me.
Did you come from outer space?
Some distant planet somewhere?
[HAND] I don't have any idea
where I came from.
My earliest memory is with you.
Feeling disappointed,
I was unable to...
occupy your brain.
My brain?! Are you kidding me?
Wait! You're not gonna go after
my brain next are you?
[HAND] If that were possible,
I would've done so already.
But sadly, it's not.
Since I've already matured
without eating your brain,
it's too late.
Most unfortunate.
[SHINICHI]
Well, what would have happened
if you had succeeded?
In eating my brain?
[HAND]
You'd probably still look pretty
much the same as you do now,
but your head would be able
to do things like this.
That's so gross!
So why, exactly,
is this happening to me?
[HAND] Pure chance.
You were not chosen
for this specifically.
(sighs) Guess I really should
go to a hospital.
Whether I'm a freakshow or not.
[HAND] A hospital? Why?
So they can cut you off,
of course.
That would be undesirable.
I rely on the nutrients
that are present
in your bloodstream
for survival.
If I were to be removed,
then I would most assuredly
shrivel up and die.
And on top of that, Shinichi,
you would end up losing your
right hand in the process.
Unfortunate for both of us.
Look! You're the one who just
took over my arm without asking.
So you don't really
have a say here.
Hmm...
How about this?
I can re‐connect the
circuitry in your arm
so that while I'm asleep you'll
be able to control your hand
just like before.
[SHINICHI] Huh?
That'll work, won't it?
The two of us are gonna have to
learn to cooperate and coexist.
It's really our only option.
Huh?
You don't get to decide
any of this!
[HAND] I'm tired. I sleep now.
Wait a minute!
Hey, you're just doing that
to get out of this discussion!
Use me with care...
(grrr...)
(sigh)
So I guess I'm supposed
to clean up this mess.
[SHINICHI]
Don't I get any bacon and eggs?
You said you didn't
want any yesterday.
[SHINICHI] I thought you told me
that I needed to eat
a proper breakfast.
And I'd like more toast too,
please.
I sure do wish you'd
make up your mind.
[IZUMI] Look at that, there've
been even more of these attacks.
Another murder?
Uh‐huh.
A mother and her daughter
were killed just last night.
Their bodies were found
"savagely mutilated",
and now it looks like the father
has disappeared without a trace.
(sizzling)
Somebody else was decapitated,
and there was another hacked up
and hung out like the
laundry!
[MOM] Can we not talk
about that right now?
Oh... yeah.
(sighs) Huh? (chuckles)
[DAD]
Hey, Shinichi, check it out.
[MOM &amp; DAD] (hmm?)
(sliding door)
[MOM] You're okay with them now?
Huh? What do you mean?
Well, that was a bug!
[HAND] Is this a different
route from yesterday?
[SHINICHI] Oh, so you're awake.
Where is it you're going?
I decided to go talk
to the police.
[HAND] Oh, don't do that.
You know they'll just take you
and turn you into their lab rat
and run all sorts of
experiments on you.
Your life will never
be the same again.
Okay, well then,
what do YOU suggest?
[HAND] I told you this morning.
Cooperation and mutual
coexistence is...
STOP!
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
Keep your voice down.
I sense one of my own.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
[HAND] Yes, one of my species.
I feel him.
There's more of you?!
Wait, how do you
know it's there?
[HAND] I just feel it...
Something like brainwaves.
It's my first time sensing it,
but I can tell:
it's definitely out there.
About 200 meters.
You mean to tell me,
someone else out there
has gone through
the same thing I have?
[HNAD] Right, go right!
[HAND] Shinichi...
[SHINICHI] Hmm? 'Kay.
[HAND] At the next
intersection, turn left.
It would seem that
they have sensed me, too.
(urk)
[HAND] What is it? Keep moving.
So, if it's one of
your species or whatever,
then could it be someone
whose brain was eaten?
[HAND] It's possible.
(uhh) Then no way!
That's too screwed up!
(waahhh!)
I would like to find out
exactly what sort of being
I actually am.
That sort of information
would be quite valuable
to you as well.
Uh... okay okay.
[HAND] Another twenty meters.
Around that corner.
It seems to be eating.
[SHINICHI] Huh?
(wet slurpling sounds)
[SHINICHI] (weakly) It's a dog,
and it's eating another dog?
(whimper of fear)
So I see... you failed too.
Please...
please don't talk, Mr. Doggy.
(uhhh...)
Your host is not... optimal.
I... also... am dissatisfied...
with... this host...
Run!
[SHINICHI] (ahh!)
[Hand] Run! Hurry!
[SHINICHI] (waahhh!)
[SHINICHI] Where are we going?!
You told me to take you there,
now you're telling me to run
away!
[HAND]
I sense its murderous intent.
You're still human;
it harbors suspicion of you.
(panting)
[HAND] It wants to fight.
We'll do it here.
What?!
You wanna fight that thing?!
[HAND] There's no choice.
If it kills you,
I will die as well.
We're in this together.
Here it comes.
What the hell?
You gotta be kidding me!
This cannot be happening!
(woorf)
(ngh!) Is that... its heart?
(heavy thump)
(low growls)
[HAND]
It will die without it. Look!
Just like me, it's dependent on
its body's digestive system
and other vital organs.
(low growls)
So I guess there really are
more of you out there.
Yes, but this one's core
was the head.
It controlled the host by
manipulating the nervous system,
but it made a crucial mistake
when it altered its body
to grow wings.
That caused its core to alter,
and its focus to disperse,
creating an opening.
But it... it was still
one of your own kind though.
[HAND]
It's because of the canine.
Maturation and environment
were factors,
but it was lax with its studies.
Research is the reason I won.
[SHINICHI] It's like I'm
talking to an insect.
Doesn't have
a shred of sympathy.
[HAND] Shinichi, that's cold.
[SHINICHI]
Not long ago, someone on Earth
had a passing thought...
"All life is sacred and must
therefore be protected."
[WOMAN] (whimpering)
(frightened breathing)
[MAN] (hyah!)
[MAN] (maniacal laughter)
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"The Devil in the Flesh"