[LITTLE BOYS] (happy)
[MOFFLE] Moff! Moff!
[MACARON]
Ro‐Ron! Ro‐Ron!
[TIRAMY]
Mii!
[WANIPEE]
(offer)
[IRONBEARD]
(laughter)
I'll be takin' this pool
fer me own!
[MERMAID]
Somebody rescue me!
[EIKO]
Oh no! The pirates are taking
that mermaid hostage!
[EIKO] What should we do?
[BOY] Let her go, meanie!
[GIRL]
I'm scared!
[IRONBEARD]
Quiet, ye barnacles...!
Cross me and ye'll all be
sleepin' with the fishes!
[MERMAID]
(shriek)
[GENJURO]
Not so fast, pirate!
[IRONBEARD]
What the blazes...?
(angry)
Curse ye, scurvy sea‐worm!
[EIKO]
Genjuro the dolphin's here
to save the day!
[EIKO] Let's give him a hand!
[BOY] Yeah, kick his butt!
[GIRL] Go, Genjuro!
[BIINO] Come get your popsicles!
[GIRL]
Wow! They look super real!
(giggling) Ew, get it away!
[ORC]
(groan)
[RUBRUM]
I far exceed human intelligence.
How dare you
raise your blade to me?
[RUBRUM]
Impudent fools!
[GIRLS]
(squeal)
[GIRL]
Omigod I love this!
Me too! How do they
do this stuff?
Welcome...
...to Amagi Brilliant Park!
The Starlight World
show starts...
...now!
[MACARON] Ron!
[MOFFLE] Moff!
[TIRAMY] Miiii!!!
[SEIYA]
The evening hours
are working out okay.
[ISUZU]
Yes... We haven't had any
issues so far.
[ISUZU]
I think it's a good move.
[KOBORY/MUSE/SALAMA/SYLPHY]
(giggle)
[SEIYA]
So how are the renewals
coming along?
[ISUZU]
Let me give you a quick update.
[FLOWER]
(hiss)
[SEIYA]
Whoa!
[ISUZU]
We added more
audience interaction.
[SEIYA]
(dodge) I don't think so!
[MACARON]
(metal scream)
[ISUZU]
Heavy metal music
is much more participatory.
[SEIYA]
Why are they all in sync?!
[BRAT B]
Sweet, guns!
[BRAT A]
Wahoo!
[BRAT C]
Let's slaughter 'em!
[MOFFLE]
Moff!
[BRAT B/BRAT A/BRAT C]
(wild excitement)
[PA VOICE] Mission completed.
[ISUZU]
This one was highly
requested by visitors.
[SEIYA]
WHICH visitors?!
[ISUZU] (horror)
[BRAT C] A girl!
[BRAT B] Yeah!
[BRAT A] Kidnap her!
[BRAT C]
Heheh!
[SEIYA]
How could every single
one of these be so terrible?
[ISUZU]
They ARE performing well
with the guests.
[SEIYA]
(annoyed)
[ISUZU]
Summer break is coming up soon,
so attendance should
keep improving.
[SEIYA]
I guess so.
[ISUZU]
(sad)
[TRIKEN]
There you are, Mr. Kanie!
(pant) I couldn't find you!
[SEIYA]
Sorry, Triken.
[TRIKEN]
The TV station is here to film.
[SEIYA]
Okay... Be right there.
[TRIKEN]
Oh and... that thing you
mentioned...
[SEIYA]
Right! Did you find something?
[TRIKEN]
Well, it doesn't look
very promising, sir.
[SEIYA]
I see.
[ISUZU]
(troubled)
Anyway... keep working hard.
[TRIKEN]
Absolutely!
[REPORTER]
What a great crowd...
especially for a weekday!
Amagi Brilliant Park is
enjoying a surge in popularity
so let's see what all the
hype's about!
[TRIKEN]
YES!
This little guy's not only cute,
but he's a super great
juggler too!
[MOFFLE] Moff, moff!
Wow...! Hey, I think
I see somebody doing
magic tricks over there!
[TRIKEN]
That reporter there certainly
has some impressive assets.
[SEIYA]
That's it. I'm gonna find
somebody else to show her
around.
[TRIKEN]
Hey! that's not fair!
More importantly, there's
a magazine coming to do a
special on us tomorrow.
You've got the schedule, right?
[TRIKEN]
Right! And I've seen tomorrow's
representative...
Her assets
are even better so...
I'll be hunched over with‐
[SEIYA]
Great.
Then I'll find somebody else
to speak with her.
[TRIKEN]
(horror)
I take it back!
[TIRAMY/MACARON]
(gulp gulp gulp)
Ahhh!
[MOFFLE]
Moff!
Hey Takami,
we're ready to order now.
[TAKAMI]
Coming!
[TIRAMY]
Hey sexy‐
[TAKAMI]
What'll it be?
[MOFFLE]
More beers, edamame,
and miso cucumbers, right?
[ISUZU]
Yes please.
[MACARON] And some octopus‐ron.
[TAKAMI] Right!
[TIRAMY]
I'll take the Takami special!
[TAKAMI] No sir.
[TIRAMY] Takami soup and salad?
[TIRAMY] Takami sandwi‐
(shot)
[TAKAMI]
Great... What else?
[MACARON]
Cold tofu‐ron.
[MOFFLE]
And maybe some omelet rolls too.
[TAKAMI]
You got it!
[MOFFLE] That'll be all.
[TAKAMI]
Thanks.
[MACARON]
I tell ya,
the drinks taste even better
now that business is so good!
We're getting more and more
visitors every day!
Right‐mii...! If this keeps up
we might not be totally doomed
after all!
[TIRAMY/MACARON]
Yeah!
(gulp! gulp! ahhhh!)
[ISUZU] Lord Moffle?
[TIRAMY]
Man, I better stop drinkin'
so much, I'm gettin' fat!
[MOFFLE]
He's right. The guest count
IS going up.
[MOFFLE] But...
[MACARON] But everybody knows
the best mascot is a chubby one!
[ISUZU] I know.
[TIRAMY] I'll put on some weight
and bring in the ladies!
[ISUZU]
At this rate,
there's a chance that...
[TIRAMY] CHUG IT!
[MACARON] Ahhh!
Now THAT'S how you knock
back a cold one,
Mac, you're a champ!
[MUSE]
Sorry we're late!
[TIRAMY]
(excited)
Hey you guys.
[SYLPHY]
Layback!
[TIRAMY]
Heyyy...
I got a seat for ya‐(shot)
[MACARON] Just sit anywhere.
[MUSE] Thanks.
[MOFFLE]
Takami, we got some more for ya!
[TAKAMI]
'Kay!
[ISUZU]
(bite)
(swallow)
[ISUZU]
They're perfect.
They're orange croquettes.
I added a little touch
of marmalade.
The tea croquettes are almost
done, so please try those too.
[ISUZU]
Of course.
[LATIFAH]
(giggle)
You know, recently...
whenever I open a window
I can hear guests and workers
laughing all the way in here.
That's lovely.
[LATIFAH]
How has Sir Kanie been lately?
He must be terribly busy.
[ISUZU]
Yes...
He's been working hard.
[LATIFAH]
(smile)
I understand.
[LATIFAH]
Oh, Lady Isuzu...?
Would you take a few of these
croquettes to Sir Kanie for me?
I'd like him
to sample them as well.
[ISUZU]
Right.
Great. They're almost
finished now...
You'll enjoy these...
I made them with Earl... Grey...
[ISUZU]
(gasp)
Your Majesty!
[LATIFAH]
(pant)
I'm alright...
I'm just feeling a little...
dizzy... nothing more...
[ISUZU]
(gasp)
Princess?! Princess!
[SEIYA]
How is she?
[ISUZU]
She's getting some rest for now.
[SEIYA]
That's good.
So what's wrong...?
Does she have
some kind of illness?
[SEIYA]
Does she...? Tell me the truth.
[MOFFLE]
No... Don't worry about it.
She'll be fine
when she's rested up.
[SEIYA]
Hey...! Moffle!
You know what's going on here,
don't you?
[SEIYA]
Say something!
[ISUZU]
(sigh)
Maple Land's residents
can't live without Animus...
...the feelings of fun and
happiness experienced
by the people of this world.
[SEIYA]
You already told me all that.
[ISUZU]
A long time ago...
Maple Land fell under attack...
by a fearsome dragon.
[SEIYA]
A dragon...?
As in a dragon like Rubrum?
[ISUZU]
It was a lot bigger than Rubrum.
[SEIYA]
Oh...
[ISUZU]
The army did
everything they could,
but they were unable
to defeat such an imposing foe.
[ISUZU]
That was when the King
was visited by a sorcerer.
He promised the King
that he would slay the dragon
in exchange for
the princess' hand in marriage.
[ISUZU]
The king agreed.
And so the sorcerer
made quick work of the dragon.
[SEIYA]
I'm guessing they didn't
live happily ever after.
[ISUZU]
The King didn't want to
surrender his daughter's hand...
so he sent the army to attack
the sorcerer.
[ISUZU]
Wounded and filled with rage,
the sorcerer placed a curse upon
the princess
that slowly drained
her Animus supply
just before he fell off a cliff.
[SEIYA]
So she's... really cursed?
[ISUZU]
(sad)
There was only one way to save
the princess from certain death.
She was sent to this world
to recuperate because there's
an abundant amount of Animus
here to keep her healthy.
[SEIYA]
And that's what the park is for.
[ISUZU]
Correct.
[SEIYA]
Which means...
if AmaBri has to shut down...!
[ISUZU]
(sigh)
She won't make it.
[SEIYA]
(breathless)
(choked up)
[SEIYA]
How do you feel?
[LATIFAH]
Sorry to make you worry.
I'll be alright
if I rest a little.
[SEIYA]
Good to hear.
[LATIFAH]
(surprised)
(sad smile)
I understand you heard about my
condition from Lady Isuzu.
Is that true?
[SEIYA]
Yeah.
[LATIFAH]
I told everyone
not to tell you...
I was afraid that you would be
worried about me if you knew it.
[LATIFAH]
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I kept it a secret,
Sir Kanie.
[SEIYA]
It's fine.
[LATIFAH]
How are things in the park
these days?
[SEIYA]
Everyone's working hard
out there.
But uh...
[LATIFAH]
Hm?
If something doesn't change...
getting enough visitors
to stay open is probably...
not possible.
[LATIFAH]
I see.
[SEIYA]
(stunned)
What's with you?
[LATIFAH]
Hm?
How can you possibly be calm
at a time like this?!
If AmaBri closes down,
you're gonna‐
(realize)
(troubled)
[LATIFAH]
(smile)
You have a point...
I know I probably won't
be alive much longer.
[SEIYA]
So why...?!
But I refuse to give up hope...
not yet.
[SEIYA]
I told you it doesn't look good.
What's the point of waiting
for a miracle that probably
won't happen?
But a miracle
already DID happen.
[SEIYA]
(surprised)
Just take a look
at everyone in the park...
Everything started changing
when you came into our lives,
[SEIYA] Really?
[LATIFAH] Yes!
You've filled our beloved park
with the smiles and laughter
of so many happy visitors
since you came to work here.
[SEIYA]
I don't know if
I would consider that a miracle.
[LATIFAH]
Sir Kanie...
I realize it may not seem
like anything special
in your eyes but...
...to me, what
you've done for us...
it means the whole world!
[SEIYA]
(surprised)
Yeah but... you're still in
serious trouble and...
(realize)
[LATIFAH]
(sad smile)
Sir Kanie?
Is everything alright?
[SEIYA]
Latifah.
Are you really okay with this?
[LATIFAH]
Yes.
Are you sure?
[LATIFAH]
(deep breath, determined)
Certainly.
(smile)
[SEIYA]
Okay then.
These ideas all suck!
[SYLPHY/MUSE/DORNELL/WANIPEE]
(startled)
[KOBORY/SALAMA]
(wince)
[WANIPEE]
B‐but the visitor count's
been getting better
since we started
working at night.
So if we stretch it
to 24 hours then‐
[SEIYA]
Yeah maybe in the long term...
But that won't make enough of a
difference before the deadline!
Unless you can give me
a clear guarantee!
[WANIPEE]
W‐well uh...
[SEIYA]
And promoting outside the park?
[DORNELL]
It's good publicity.
[SEIYA]
Advertising takes way too long
to bring in actual results...!
We don't have time
for stuff like that!
[SEIYA]
For right now,
we have to do whatever it takes
to get that visitor count up!
And you!
[SEIYA] The 0 yen campaign!
[MUSE/KOBORY] (startled)
That's no different from the
30 yen push we're doing NOW...!
It won't give us
enough of a boost!
[MUSE]
(nervous)
You're right; I'm sorry
that's a dumb idea...
[SEIYA]
It's almost July 31st...
What this park needs right now
is a solid idea that'll
guarantee 134,000 guests
before then.
Come up with something better!
[WANIPEE]
He was outta line!
It wasn't nice of him to yell at
us when we're trying to help!
[SYLPHY] (happy humming)
[SALAMA] Yeah that was #rude.
[MUSE]
Calm down, you guys...
[KOBORY]
I don't know.
maybe something's
been bothering him.
[DORNELL]
He's just aggro
over the deadline.
[SALAMA]
(pouting)
[KOBORY]
(realize)
The classic boy‐in‐a
desperate‐situation scenario!
[SYLPHY]
Oooooh... Aaaahhhh...
[KOBORY]
We should pair him with a guy
who's more experienced!
[DORNELL] It's not a BL manga...
[SALAMA] Hit Like if you agree!
[MUSE] Let's get going.
[SYLPHY] Moscow Mule!
[MOFFLE]
You're making
a lot of enemies lately.
[SEIYA]
I know!
But if I don't pull out
all the stops,
we're not gonna sell enough
tickets before the deadline.
[MOFFLE]
Gettin' all moffin' mad
won't help.
[ISUZU]
Everybody's trying
their hardest.
[SEIYA]
(smile)
I don't need you to
tell me that.
[MOFFLE]
(annoyed)
But if we don't have something
to show for it,
they might as well
be doing nothing!
[MOFFLE]
What happened to
what you said before?
"Whatever it takes
to get even one more guest"?
[SEIYA]
You're right...
That kinda crap
is why we're about to fail!
[MOFFLE]
Moff!
[ISUZU]
Lord Moffle!
[SEIYA]
Even if AmaBri closes down,
the cast members
can find another job.
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
[SEIYA]
But Latifah's not so lucky.
[MOFFLE]
(surprised)
You told him, didn't you, Isuzu?
[ISUZU]
Yes.
[MOFFLE]
(small sigh)
[SEIYA]
(angry)
I'm exhausted.
[AISU]
Working too hard, huh?
Something like that.
[AISU]
(sigh)
(gulp)
Ahhh...
[SEIYA]
Hey Aunt Aisu?
[AISU]
Yeah?
[SEIYA]
Being a magazine editor...
is it hard?
[AISU]
Not really.
Except when the
manuscripts are late and the
printers get pissed.
And sometimes authors
straight‐up run from us.
[SEIYA]
(sigh)
So uh...
whenever something
goes wrong at work...
what do you do about it?
[AISU]
Grab a beer and forget it!
[SEIYA]
What?!
[TEACHER]
Now, have a safe summer break
and set the best example you can
for your fellow students, okay?
You're excused.
[GIRL]
Don't forget your books!
[MOFFLE]
You're 10 years too young to be
lookin' this depressed, Kid.
[SEIYA]
What's this about?
[MOFFLE]
Don't worry about it.
[SEIYA]
(sigh)
[MOFFLE]
That'll cost ya.
[SEIYA]
(spit take)
You expect me to pay?!
[MOFFLE]
Just moffin' ya.
(drinking)
[SEIYA]
I really can't stand you.
You know that?
[MOFFLE]
(ahh) Right back atcha.
I don't get it.
[SEIYA]
What do you mean?
[MOFFLE]
Why are you so desperate
to fix this?
[SEIYA]
I met Latifah a long time ago.
[MOFFLE]
Moff?
[SEIYA]
When I was a kid.
I wandered into
the garden by mistake...
She was sitting there crying.
[SEIYA]
When I asked her what was wrong,
she told me some story
about a sorcerer's curse...
and how she was really lonely.
[MOFFLE]
She told you?
[SEIYA]
Yeah.
I wanted her to stop crying
so I showed her my impression of
the legendary Prince Shotoku‐
[MOFFLE]
What‐?! I wanna see!
[SEIYA]
Not now.
[MOFFLE]
(angry spit)
[SEIYA]
What's your problem?
As I was saying,
I was so desperate to put
a smile on her face that day.
But I failed.
[MOFFLE]
You failed?
[SEIYA]
Well, she did smile
when she saw my impression...
...but it was a sad smile.
Like she was just trying
to make me feel better.
[MOFFLE]
That's the
kind of person she is.
[SEIYA]
When I saw that...
I promised Latifah that
I would find a way to save her.
[SEIYA]
Come to think of it...
I was noticing that she looks
exactly the same
as she did when I first met her
all those years ago.
Do the people of Maple Land
just not age or something?
[MOFFLE]
Latifah's a special case.
That curse does more
than make her weak.
[SEIYA]
(listen)
Every year, it erases a whole
year's worth of memories and
physical growth,
which makes her eternally young.
[SEIYA]
(stunned)
Wha...?
[MOFFLE]
For more than a decade now,
she's been living
as a 14‐year‐old girl.
[SEIYA]
(quiet shock)
So that's why her looks
haven't changed since we met.
[MOFFLE]
That's right.
August 1st is the anniversary
of Latifah's curse.
[MOFFLE]
And when that day gets here,
she'll forget you too.
[SEIYA]
(gasp)
(choked up)
[SEIYA]
Who cares... if she forgets me?
[MOFFLE]
Moff?
[SEIYA]
This is my problem to solve.
After I was lucky enough
to be given another chance
to make Latifah smile.
[SEIYA]
I can't fail her again.
Wait and see... I can do this!
[MOFFLE]
Moff...
[SEIYA]
Why do YOU care
so much about Latifah?
Because Latifah's my niece,
of course.
[SEIYA]
Like, by blood?!
[MOFFLE]
Yeah. What about it?
[SEIYA]
(comic horror)
Never mind.
[MOFFLE]
Not long ago...
the plan was to take her with me
when the park closed down
and become a street performer.
[MOFFLE]
I figured a simple life
like that wouldn't be so bad.
Even if it couldn't
last for long.
[MOFFLE]
I'd accepted it.
But when you showed up,
you changed my mind.
Even if we go down...
I want to fight
to the moffin' end.
[MOFFLE]
What are you gonna do?
[SEIYA]
(smile)
Right!
(door open)
[TRIKEN]
(pant)
I found one...!
I did it, Mr. Kanie!
We just might reach
our goal after all!
[SEIYA]
(happy)
[ISUZU/SEIYA]
Time for the
attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU]
Today we have
Rubrum's Chamber of Trials.
[SEIYA]
We've been to this one before,
but I'm glad to see it's getting
more popular these days.
[ISUZU]
The traps we fell into
the first time are still intact.
Rubrum's excited to have
more work to do as well.
[SEIYA]
Are the prison cells
still there?
[ISUZU]
Yes. I hear the
hospitality's so good
that some visitors refuse
to leave at the end of the day.
[SEIYA]
It's not a hotel!