[EIKO]
And so peace was restored to the
enchanted forest.
And the miracle brought about
by the four spirits
became known as
the Legend of Elementario!
[MUSE]
(small effort x4)
[MUSE/SALAMA] (impact)
[KOBORY] Wh‐whoaaa!
[SALAMA] Ah, jeez...
[MUSE]
Thank you everyone!
See you soon!
[KOBORY]
W‐we hope you liked the
performance...
[SALAMA]
Yeah! whatever.
[SYLPHY]
Dhanyavadah te!
[SEIYA]
This is terrible.
[ISUZU]
It seems the four of you don't
know the meaning of harmony.
[MUSE]
We're sorry.
[MOFFLE]
Moff... Do you even get along
with each other?
[MUSE]
Why would the princess
invite us all to dinner?
[SALAMA]
Maybe we're about to get fired.
[KOBORY]
Oh! I certainly hope not...
[MUSE]
(smile)
(notice)
What is it, Sylphy?
[KOBORY]
Is it just me or does this tree
have more flowers
than it did before?
[MUSE]
Now that you mention it...
[LATIFAH]
Welcome!
[KOBORY]
The princess.
I'm so glad you all could
attend!
[LATIFAH]
Please help yourselves
to whatever you like.
[MUSE]
Thank you so much Your Highness!
[SYLPHY]
Don't mind if I do!
Ahhh...
(bite)
[MUSE]
So uh... Your Majesty?
[LATIFAH]
Yes?
Why did you invite us here?
[LATIFAH]
Well... I heard from Sir Kanie
that you ladies
were having difficulties
rehearsing your new show.
So I invited you over
for sukiyaki.
I thought it might
help you relax.
[MUSE]
That's the reason?
[LATIFAH]
Of course!
[SALAMA]
Sheesh who cares why?
[MUSE]
(surprised)
Don't say that, Salama!
That's rude, and you shouldn't
be messing around
on your phone
in front of Her Majesty!
[SALAMA]
Fine. Sorry, princess,
I just need to finish this post.
[MUSE]
(annoyed)
Oh dear! Perhaps this wasn't a
good idea after all.
[MUSE]
No! of course it is.
we're having a great time!
[MUSE]
Having fun, Kobory?
[KOBORY]
(eager nod)
Sylphy too... Tell her!
[SYLPHY]
Oishii ne!
[MUSE]
And Salama might LOOK bored‐
but check out what she's typing!
She's raving about it!
[LATIFAH]
(nervous laugh)
Alright then! if you're certain.
[SALAMA]
Come on Muse,
quit acting so prim and proper.
I'm sure the princess would want
us to be upfront with each other
whether she's listening or not!
[MUSE]
(surprised)
[LATIFAH]
(smile)
You all formed your
performance troupe
less than six months ago.
Isn't that correct?
[MUSE]
Y‐yes...
The original performers
quit out of nowhere
so they asked us to replace
them.
You know! Moffle and the others
were the ones
who suggested
we meet like this.
[KOBORY]
That's right!
He does
like to bond over drinks.
[SALAMA]
That's so lame.
Why do you have to say
such negative things?
Mr. Moffle's obviously
worried about us!
[SALAMA]
(annoyed) Well sorry...
Little Miss Goody Two‐Shoes.
[MUSE]
(offended) At least
I KNOW how to be nice.
[KOBORY] No! stop...
please don't fight! okay?
[SALAMA] Yeah, sure you do.
[MUSE]
What's that supposed to mean?
[KOBORY] Sylphy! make them stop.
[SALAMA]
Like you're being extra nice
in front of the princess.
[MUSE]
Will you drop it?
You should be honored to!
[LATIFAH]
(gasp)
Please excuse me! ladies.
But unfortunately, this is
all the sauce we have left.
[MUSE]
Okay, then I'll just‐!
[LATIFAH]
No!
I have to be a proper hostess
for my guests.
But we couldn't possibly
make you go out!
[LATIFAH]
It's quite alright...
Please wait here.
[MUSE]
(speechless)
(overdramatic gasp)
[MUSE]
What's the matter,
Your Highness?
[LATIFAH]
I almost forgot to tell you all
something very important.
[LATIFAH]
That red button over there...
Whatever you do,
please do not touch it.
[MUSE]
Um... okay?
[LATIFAH]
It controls a crucial mechanism.
Am I clear?
No matter what happens,
you must never
touch that button.
[MUSE]
(gulp)
Great. Now I'm starting
to get curious.
[KOBORY]
I wonder what would happen
if we touched it.
[SALAMA]
Welp! Only one way to find out!
Djdjdjdjdjdj!
Stop it Salama,
she said not to!
WHAT PART OF 'STOP IT'
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?!
[KOBORY]
Ah! (impact) Whoaaaa!
[SYLPHY]
(happy chewing)
[SALAMA]
Ow!
[MUSE]
(startled)
Hey watch it! Aaah!
[MUSE] (panicking)
[SALAMA] (scared)
[KOBORY] (hand‐over‐mouth fret)
[LATIFAH]
Oh goodness! what's happening?
(gasp x 2)
(worried)
(surprised)
It couldn't be!
(gasp)
[OKURO]
(running)
(panic)
[OKURO]
Luchaaa!
[SEIYA]
There's an automated
defense mode?
[LATIFAH]
Yes. As soon as someone
activates it‐
the system automatically
eradicates
anyone or anything attempting to
gain entry to the castle.
[SEIYA]
Why would a theme park castle
come equipped with
such a dangerous system?
[LATIFAH]
Because...
It's designed for Princess
Latifah's protection...
You never know when an enemy
might try to infiltrate.
[TRIKEN]
Right! Aim to the right!
[ISUZU]
She's a member of
the Maple Land royal family...
so we have to take
the necessary precautions.
[MACARON]
Chaaarge!
[ISUZU]
The automatic cannons
are devastatingly accurate.
[SEIYA]
But wait‐ the four spirits
are inside the castle.
Maybe we can get
in touch with them somehow.
[ISUZU]
Apparently they have
internet access,
but they're not able
to get out of the room.
[SEIYA]
Ugh, great,
the whole point of this thing
is to protect Latifah,
but she's sitting
outside with us.
What good does that do?
[LATIFAH]
Ah...
[ISUZU]
In any case,
it'll be impossible to get past
that cannon without casualties.
[TIRAMY]
(weak)
[SEIYA]
(sigh) So what,
it's gonna be like this forever?
[ISUZU]
No...
It says here that the system
deactivates after 24 hours.
All we can do for now
is wait it out, I suppose.
[SEIYA]
Until 9PM tomorrow?
[ISUZU]
Yes...
It'll fire on anyone
who gets
close to the castle,
which means we have no choice
but to close the park
in the meantime.
[SEIYA]
Seriously?! Tomorrow's Saturday!
The visitor count's been on a
steady climb,
we're not closing a whole day.
[WANIPEE]
This wasn't supposed to happen.
[ISUZU]
You'd rather endanger guests?
[WANIPEE]
We were gonna get married
[GENJURO]
She's not your girlfriend!
[MOFFLE]
Hmph... What a buncha
moffin' amateurs.
[SEIYA]
Moffle?
Leave this to me, you hear?
[SEIYA]
What are you planning to do?
[MOFFLE]
I can't attack from the ground,
but I've still got the sky!
[MOFFLE]
Rubrum!
[RUBRUM]
(awkward howl)
Sorry...
I'm sort of an
indoor‐type dragon
so flying's
not really my thing...
[MOFFLE]
Yeah, well it's about to be!
Let's go!
[RUBRUM]
O‐okay!
[MOFFLE]
Lightning God Blast Technique!
[RUBRUM]
(amazed) Incredible!
[MOFFLE]
Hmph... piece o' moffin' cake.
Alright! I'd better‐
[RUBRUM]
(panic)
M‐Mr. Moffle!
[MOFFLE/MACARON/TIRAMY]
We didn't make it.
[SEIYA]
Obviously.
[ISUZU]
That means all we can do now
is try to flip the emergency
stop switch from the inside.
[SEIYA]
Emergency stop switch?
If it was that easy then why
didn't you say so in the first
place!
[MOFFLE/MACARON/TIRAMY]
(raging)
[ISUZU]
It would seem there's a hidden
passage in Her Majesty's
bedroom.
[MOFFLE/MACARON/TIRAMY]
(pout)
It leads to the room where
the switch is located.
[LATIFAH]
Oh really?
I wasn't aware of that!
[ISUZU]
Yes...
It also says that activating
the switch requires four people.
[SEIYA]
And you didn't know?
[LATIFAH]
(surprised)
Well, I suppose there's
a possIbility that
I knew about it previously.
[SEIYA]
Hm?
[ISUZU]
Then the best course of action
is to try to get
in contact with them.
[MUSE]
Light blue vase, got it.
You just want me to turn it?
Okay then... If you say so.
(determined)
[KOBORY]
(startled) What's that?
[MUSE]
Wow...
[KOBORY]
So the emergency stop switch
is at the end of this tunnel?
[MUSE]
That's what she told me.
But I wonder why it needs
four people?
[MUSE]
"The first challenge."
Well, here goes.
[KOBORY]
Be careful, Muse.
[MUSE]
Huh?
[KOBORY/SALAMA/MUSE/SYLPHY]
What IS this?!
[SALAMA]
Why is there a
karaoke room in here?
[KOBORY]
Who knows?
[MUSE/SALAMA]
(startled)
[MUSE]
"All four have to sing
to reach 300 points"...
Oh, gosh...
What do they mean by
"painful punishment"?
[TIRAMY]
Anddd there!
I think I set this thing up
right, mii.
[MACARON]
I see the girls‐ron!
[MUSE]
FUN!TASY Time, FUN! TASY Fly,
FUN!TASY World, oh yeah!
[SEIYA]
[Why] Are they singing karaoke?
[ISUZU]
In order to reach the stop
switch...
the four of them have to
overcome a series of challenges.
[MUSE]
FUN!TASY Time, FUN! TASY Fly,
FUN! TASY World, oh yeah!
[ISUZU]
The first one is karaoke.
[MUSE]
I can always tell when
you've been thinkin'
[TIRAMY]
Muse is killin' it‐mii!
[LATIFAH]
At this rate,
they're sure to succeed!
[ISUZU]
I'm not so sure.
[SEIYA]
Why is that?
Whether or not they pass
is based
on the total
of all their scores.
Which means that if even one
is a poor singer,
the entire
operation will fail.
[KOBORY]
If you're too afraid to go,
there's no way you'll ever know
[KOBORY]
It's not hard to learn the
dance, if you take a chance
[KOBORY]
Hold on tight to what you love,
like a precious little dove
[KOBORY]
It can set you free,
just believe me
[MUSE/KOBORY]
It's a wonderful wonderful
wonderful wonderful world
just for you
[TIRAMY]
They're surprisingly
good singers!
[MACARON]
Yeah! I thought Kobory‐ron
was dull as a wet paper bag.
[SEIYA]
That was uncalled for...
[MOFFLE]
Moff, that's a
pretty good score so far.
[MUSE/KOBORY]
And it lives
inside of you and me
[MUSE/KOBORY]
Catch my heart
FUN!TASY Time, FUN! TASY Fly,
[MACARON]
Looks like Sylphy‐ron's up next.
[SYLPHY]
Couldn't bear to see you
looking so sad
All I wanted was
to take you by the hand
[MACARON]
Hmm... her voice is unique,
but not bad.
[ISUZU]
Uniqueness won't get her
a high score.
[LATIFAH]
But everything should be alright
if she gets a DECENT score.
[LATIFAH]
Let's see how Salama performs.
[SALAMA (Badly)]
Hadn't seen you in a while,
but you wouldn't even smile
[SALAMA (Badly)]
Made me wanna take that frown,
turn it upside down
[SEIYA]
Oh my god... It's over.
[TIRAMY]
I always wondered why she
never came with us to karaoke
but I think I get it now.
[LATIFAH]
Poor Salama.
They can still make it if she
racks up at least 50 points.
[SALAMA (Badly)/SYLPHY]
It's a wonderful wonderful
wonderful wonderful world
just for you
[SALAMA (Badly)/SYLPHY]
And just when you think
you've seen it all,
you'll find something new
[SALAMA/KOBORY/MUSE/SYLPHY]
(scream)
[SEIYA]
Am I supposed to be able to
see their skeletons?!
[ISUZU]
Unfortunately,
they failed the challenge.
[MACARON]
Hey look, I think Muse‐ron's
ready to try again.
[KOBORY]
Oh no...
I guess we have no choice
but to give it another go.
[SALAMA]
What good will that do?!
I'm so sorry you guys‐
I'm just not a good singer.
[MUSE]
Don't you worry...
I've got you!
[SALAMA]
(amazed)
[MUSE]
Feel the wind and kiss the rain,
let them take away the pain
[MUSE]
Think of flowers every day,
or a flame that lights your way
[MUSE]
Every miracle here on Earth,
can't you see what they're worth
Your dreams can be reality
[SEIYA] Much better.
[LATIFAH] She sings so
beautifully!
[MUSE]
If you only believe
It's a wonderful wonderful
wonderful wonderful world
just for you
[MUSE]
And just when you think
you've seen it all,
you'll find something new
It's a wonderful wonderful
wonderful wonderful world
don't you see
And it lives inside
of you and me
Catch my heart!
[SALAMA/KOBORY/MUSE/SYLPHY]
We did it!
[SEIYA]
A hundred points?!
I knew Muse would be
enough to pull them through!
[SALAMA/MUSE]
(realize)
[SALAMA]
Um... thanks for that.
[MUSE]
Oh, sure.
"All four have to dance
to reach 300 points."
Again with the punishment?!
[KOBORY]
Oh no!! Anything but dancing!
[SALAMA]
At least it's not more singing.
[MOFFLE]
Interesting, so Kobory's
the weakest link this time.
[TIRAMY]
Yeah that girl couldn't dance
if her life depended on it.
[SEIYA]
That's too bad since that's
EXACTLY what's happening here.
[SYLPHY]
(cheerful)
[SALAMA]
(light efforts)
[KOBORY]
(stumbling)
It's moving too fast!
I can't keep up!
[MUSE]
(happy)
[SYLPHY]
[SALAMA]
(happy)
[KOBORY]
(worried)
[MUSE]
Ha!
[SALAMA/SYLPHY]
Hup!
[KOBORY]
(awkward)
[SALAMA/SYLPHY/MUSE/KOBORY]
(impact, coughing)
[SALAMA]
Flour of all things?
[KOBORY]
I'm so sorry!
[MOFFLE]
Saw that comin' a mile away.
[LATIFAH]
But they're working so hard‐
this isn't fair at all! (pout)
[SEIYA]
I still don't understand why
an emergency security system
needs a goofy entertainment
feature like this.
[ISUZU]
Whoever designed this castle
a long time ago
seemed to think it was
necessary.
Perhaps they thought
it was appropriate
since this is a theme park.
[KOBORY]
(struggling)
[KOBORY/SYLPHY/SALAMA/MUSE]
(coughing)
[SALAMA]
Not again!
[MUSE]
(cough)
[KOBORY]
(pant)
I knew I would fail this...
[SYLPHY]
I got your back!
[KOBORY]
(huh?) (look)
[SYLPHY]
(giggle)
[KOBORY]
I sure hope so.
[SALAMA]
(giggle)
[MUSE]
[KOBORY]
(unsure) (smile)
[MUSE]
(giggle)
[SALAMA]
Yeah!
[SYLPHY]
(giggle)
[KOBORY]
(happy)
[KOBORY/SYLPHY/SALAMA/MUSE]
(excited)
[SYLPHY]
Mhm!
[KOBORY] (look)
[SYLPHY] (smile)
[SEIYA]
They managed to get
through another round.
That's interesting.
They've all got different
strengths and weaknesses
don't they‐ron?
Watching those brave girls put
their heads together
to help each other succeed
is truly touching!
[MOFFLE]
There's still a chance they
could moff up the next round.
[MUSE]
"Aim for 300 points
by how fast you can type"?
[MUSE]
(panic)
Um... ah...!
[SYLPHY]
(focusing)
[MUSE]
(scared)
[SYLPHY/MUSE/KOBORY/SALAMA]
(impact)
These penalties
are starting to feel lazy.
[TIRAMY]
Muse is the worst typist
I've ever seen‐mii.
[MACARON]
But Salama‐ron's
finally found her true calling.
[SALAMA]
(focusing)
Got it!
[MUSE]
(painful impact)
(horror)
[SALAMA]
(concentrating)
There!
[MUSE/KOBORY]
(flinch)
[KOBORY]
(realize)
Wow! look at Salama's points.
[MUSE]
(huh?)
[KOBORY] She maxed out!
[SALAMA]
Aww yeah!
[KOBORY]
We passed! Salama, you saved us!
[MUSE] (whimper)
[SALAMA] Eh, it was nothing.
[KOBORY]
No, really, you were great!
[MUSE]
(slapped) (huh?)
(smile)
[MOFFLE]
Tough little moffers
aren't they?
[MACARON]
Everything's so perfect
it's kinda boring.
[TIRAMY]
I agree! I would've expected 'em
to give up a long time ago‐mii.
[SEIYA]
You guys suck.
Well, according to the
manual...
this is the final challenge.
[MUSE]
I guess we're each supposed
to get into one of these pods.
[SYLPHY]
(amazed)
[MUSE]
Here goes.
"Sacrifice"... Huh? (shriek)
[KOBORY] (shocked)
[SYLPHY] (huh?)
[SALAMA] (stunned)
[KOBORY]
I don't like this at all!
The system will prompt each
person
to vote for one of their peers‐
and whoever gets the most votes
will fall victim
to a giant drill.
[ISUZU] But wait...
[SEIYA] What is it?
[ISUZU]
If none of the candidates
are voted for more than once,
then all four drills
will be deactivated
and everyone will be
released immediately.
So basically if they all
want to make it out in one piece
the safest strategy is for
everybody to vote for themselves
as the sacrifice, right?
[MOFFLE]
But they can't see each other,
so if even one of them
betrays the other,
somebody dies.
[MUSE]
What should I do?
Choose a sacrifice...
Maybe I should choose myself?
Or...
[MUSE]
I should...
(sob)
Right.
All I want is for the four of us
to stand in the spotlight
together again.
[MUSE]
That's why...
(surprised)
[MUSE/SALAMA/KOBORY/SYLPHY]
(happy)
[MUSE]
(happy x2)
(smile)
[ALL]
(giggles)
[TIRAMY]
Oh! come on
that was a total copout‐mii!
[MACARON]
Yeah! where's the bloodshed‐ron!
[MOFFLE]
Shut up, you two,
I'm glad it worked out.
[LATIFAH]
What a beautiful ending this is!
[SEIYA]
I guess that sukiyaki
worked its magic after all.
[ISUZU]
They opened up to each other.
[SEIYA]
Yeah.
Alright, get all cast members
besides the rescue squad
over to the castle
so they can fix things up.
[SEIYA]
We're about to be busy.
[EIKO]
And so peace was restored
to the enchanted forest.
And the miracle brought about
by the four spirits
became known as the
Legend of Elementario!
[MUSE]
(dance exert)
[SALAMA]
[KOBORY]
(happy)
[SYLPHY]
(cheering)
[MUSE]
Thank you! everybody!
[KOBORY]
We hope you enjoyed
the show today!
[SALAMA]
See ya again soon dudes!
[SYLPHY]
Dhanyavadah te!
[ISUZU]
Their show sold out today.
The other attractions are
gaining in popularity as well.
[LATIFAH]
Wonderful.
It seems there may still be
a miracle in store for us.
[ISUZU]
(troubled)
[LATIFAH]
Remember, Lady Isuzu...
there's one thing
you mustn't tell Sir Kanie.
[ISUZU]
Of course.
[ISUZU/SEIYA]
Time for the attractions
spotlight.
[ISUZU]
I'm sure you're familiar
with Maple Castle now.
Princess Latifah resides here.
[SEIYA]
Does it really need all those
extra security features?
[ISUZU]
The king of Maple Land
has a tendency to worry...
His life motto has always been
"better safe than sorry."
[SEIYA]
Maybe we can make that alarm
system
into something interesting
for the guests.
[ISUZU]
It costs us 2 million yen
every time it goes off.
[SEIYA]
Whoa, nevermind!