[birds singing]
[LATIFAH]
Oh, no, it's all right.
I just got a little dizzy
and fell down.
I was worried.
I heard you fainted,
so I came running.
[giggle]
Everyone here can be so
dramatic sometimes.
But I do appreciate you
being concerned for me.
As you might've guessed,
Her Majesty's health is
in critical condition.
[SEIYA] (sigh) Let me guess:
because I made her go out in
that stupid swimsuit, right?
[MOFFLE]
I don't think that's it.
[ISUZU] Listen...
This does happen
from time to time,
so keep it in mind.
[MACARON] Ron‐ron‐ron...
Mi, mi, miii!
[MOFFLE]
Moff, moff, moff... Moff!
[KIDS] (cheers & laughing)
[SEIYA] Perfect, the mascots are
really stepping up their game.
That's true, but some of them
aren't quite as motivated
as the others.
Please tell me the
visitor count's up today.
It's rising. The 30 yen
campaign must be working. Huh?
[ground rumbling]
[ALL] (huh?!)
[KIDS] (cheering)
Incoming!
[KIDS] (cheers & squealing)
[BRAT A] Field trip!
[BRAT B] Yeah!
[BRAT C] Let's beat 'em up!
[KIDS] (cheering & laughing)
[MASCOTS] (waaahh!)
[ISUZU] Field trip groups
are always a challenge.
[KIDS] (cheering & laughing)
This is brutal.
We should help.
[KIDS] (cheering & laughing)
[SEIYA] You okay?
Yes.
[KIDS] (cheering & laughing)
They're the same as
any other customers.
What? Is this too hard for you?
Of course not!
Don't be ridiculous.
You just watch.
Thank you for visiting AmaBri.
Is there anything
I can help you with?
[BRAT A] A girl!
[BRAT C] (evil laugh)
[BRATS] (maniacal laughter)
[BRAT B] Gimme, lady!
Hurry, there's a long
list of issues that need
to be addressed.
I AM hurrying.
We have to see the Sales
Department about the
new info board...
I know. We're on the way.
Oh...
I apologize for troubling you.
I just wanted to talk about
the new info board.
Do you have a design yet?
Yes, I've got
five drafts right here.
None of these work.
Huh?! Oh, dear...
But, Kanie, it took him a whole
week to create those designs.
Let me try.
See,
this is how you need to do it.
[SEIYA] One... two... three.
Much better!
[TRIKEN] Oh my, yes!
I quite agree.
[ISUZU] (hmmm)
I bow to your
superior expertise!
You can iron out the details.
Hurry up, Sento, let's go.
Jeez, Manager,
what took ya so long?
Sorry. So, how's the stock?
This is all we've got left.
[SEIYA] (hmm...)
At this rate, we're gonna be
outta food by next week!
And the usual supplier couldn't
do anything to help us out.
Okay, then we'll just have
to look for a new supplier.
We should try to come up with a
solution before next we‐
[SEIYA] Amagi Brilliant Park...
[ISUZU] (huh?)
This is Kanie.
I spoke with you before.
We do need your help after all.
I'll pass the phone to the
chief of food service.
Huh?
Go on, order what you need.
[NICK] Uh, thanks I guess.
Keep moving, Sento.
[ASHE] Some expenses on the
budget estimate might be...
a little unnecessary.
And what are those?
All of these have to do
with costume repair.
If you look at‐ [uh?]
So you mean this,
this, and this?
[ah!] Yes, sir.
[SEIYA] It's not unnecessary.
Leave it on there.
Right, I'll do that.
[SEIYA] What's next?
These ol' pumps are startin' to
get mighty rickety here lately,
Manager.
[ISUZU] Then, we'll
contact the manufacturer‐
We're too broke.
Shut one of them down
and use the parts
to run the other two.
Are you sure?
What'll we do
if something goes wrong?
That's a problem for later.
Whatever you say, boss.
[SEIYA] Next!
[ISUZU] We're running out of
space for merchandise.
[MER] (urgh...)
[SEIYA] This spot's free.
Move it all there.
[MER] (exasperated sigh)
[ISUZU] Our security
equipment is broken.
[SEIYA] Hyah!
No, it isn't!
The guests don't like the
liver and chive stir‐fry.
[SEIYA] Change the recipe!
[ISUZU] His favorite pop star
spent the night with a man.
Toss out the damn magazine.
[sigh]
What's next on the agenda?
[ISUZU] Finishing this
stack of paperwork,
and then a meeting about
which attractions to renew.
A meeting? Who's going?
[ISUZU] Just Moffle,
Macaron, and Tiramy.
Great, those three. Maybe I'll
leave the meeting to you.
[ISUZU] Are you sure?
I'm exhausted as it is.
I don't have the energy
for those clowns today.
Just Let me take care
of the paperwork.
[ISUZU] As you wish.
Hey, Sento?
Try to make everything
go smoothly, okay?
You understand?
I don't need you
to explain that to me.
Huh? You okay, Sento?
What's her problem?
[MUSE] Um, excuse us, sir!
The door's open; come on in.
Uh... (nervous giggle)
[SYLPHY] (humming)
What's up?
[MUSE] Well, uh, it's kind
of a sensitive problem, sir,
but we were hoping we could
talk to you for a minute?
Actually, I'm pretty busy
figuring out all this
paperwork right now.
Maybe you should go talk
to Sento about it?
Nah, if we could talk to her,
then we wouldn't have
bothered with you.
Oh, no, she didn't mean that
the way it sounded!
We just wanted to come
speak to you directly.
[SEIYA] So what's the problem?
Uh, well, you see, sir,
it's just that, um...
[KOBORY] (nervous cowering)
[sigh] All right fine, you win.
You just tell me what you want.
Okay, let's see, how can I
explain this delicately?
Um, maybe we'd better let him
see it for himself.
Oh, that's a good idea!
Can we borrow you
for a bit, sir?
This is embarrassing.
It's all busted up!
What's it gonna take
to convince you
to invest in some
new equipment?!
I can't. I told you
we don't have the money.
Come on! The kids aren't gonna
wanna play with an old broken
water gun like this!
As a mascot, you have control
over the guests' experience.
You'll just have to blow them
away with your charisma.
"Blow them away"?!
And I have more than enough of
these bullets to go around.
Moffu...
[SYLPHY] (awahhhh...)
[SEIYA] (sigh)
I can't work like this!
My accordi‐ron broke
and I need a new one!
[ISUZU] No, make do with
your other instruments.
Aw, man! But the whole audience
is gonna run for the hills!
Well, if that happens,
then you'll just have
to run them down.
"Run them down"?
I want you to take your
job seriously. Got that?
Ron...
Hey, look at this!
[gun shot]
[TIRAMY] (ungh!)
What are you asking for?
[TIRAMY]
Oops, wrong thing. Here!
This talking flower broke.
I think it might be dead!
Maybe we can save it!
No we can't. Deal with it.
But... but... [wahh!]
[ISUZU] I said deal.
[TIRAMY] (hysterical sobbing)
Bon appétit? Oui!
She's been acting weird!
We can't ask her for anything.
[ISUZU] What's this about?
[BOTH] (ah!)
[MUSE] Nothing, nothing at all!
[KOBORY] We were only
making conversation!
I'll listen to all
your complaints.
There's no need for you
to bother Kanie.
We didn't!
We just wanted to...
Sento, let's talk.
[SYLPHY] Comment allez‐vous?
I told you to make sure
things went smoothly.
[ISUZU] Right, I prevented any
conflicts from arising.
Prevented? You just threatened
them all into submission.
Just like the time you forced me
to come to this park.
[ummm]
You can't threaten people.
You have to find a way to
compromise with them.
What you're doing is oppressive
and it has to stop.
What? Don't you think YOU'RE
being oppressive too?!
Oh, I am, but I make sure
they understand the reason why.
[ISUZU] (hmpf!)
I sure hope this isn't the
way you handled conflicts
when you were the acting
manager for a year.
You think that's any
of your business?!
Yes!
[ISUZU] (wah?)
[SEIYA] You're my secretary now.
I'm not gonna let you keep
dragging me down like this.
You think that I drag you down?
Really?
At this rate, yeah.
[ISUZU] (arrgh!)
[SEIYA] (urk!)
Okay, then what else can I
possibly be doing?!
Sento...
[ISUZU] (huh?)
[SEIYA] Sento, wait!
Seriously, what's her deal?
[sob]
[knock on door]
[LATIFAH] Yes? Come in.
Latifah, are you‐ [ah!]
[LATIFAH] (urk!)
Oh, S‐Sir Kanie?!
[SEIYA] Oh, crap... Sorry.
[LATIFAH] It's all right.
You surprised me.
Are you feeling any better,
ma'am?
[LATIFAH] I've been getting a
little restless in here,
so I was just about to go
outside and take in
some fresh air.
[SEIYA] Oh, okay, that sounds
like a good idea.
Well, actually, would you mind
giving me a moment of
your time, please?
[LATIFAH] This old ride
is still so lovely.
[SEIYA] Yeah...
[LATIFAH] (ah!)
I've wanted to ride it with
you for a while now.
It almost feels like
we're out on a date.
Uh, I guess so...
[LATIFAH] Look,
there's the main entrance.
[SEIYA] (ugh!)
[LATIFAH]
Oh, and there's Etcet Land.
[SEIYA] Uh‐huh...
[LATIFAH] And Wild Valley's
right next to it, and...
Yeah...
Uh, are you all right there?
Sure I am.
Man, just look at that view!
Is it possible you're
afraid of h‐
No way! As if somebody as
awesome as me would
have that problem!
[forced laugh]
[metal clanking & groaning]
[LATIFAH] Sir Kanie?
S‐sorry, but to tell the truth
I'm EXTREMELY afraid of heights.
There's no need to fear.
Try to relax.
I'm so sorry.
If I had known about this,
I wouldn't have asked you
to come with me.
[SEIYA]
My ego got the best of me.
It wasn't your fault.
[LATIFAH] But...
Anyway, you think we could
just keep this between us?
[LATIFAH] Of course.
Wouldn't it be pertinent to at
least tell Lady Isuzu about it?
Are you kidding me?!
ESPECIALLY not her!
Ah, right.
[SEIYA] (sigh)
[LATIFAH] (giggle)
[SEIYA] (huh?)
[LATIFAH] I apologize for
laughing, it's just so funny...
[LATIFAH] (giggling)
[SEIYA] (umm)
Hey, Latifah?
[LATIFAH] Yes?
Is there some chance we knew
each other a long time ago?
You're asking if
we've met before?
[SEIYA] Yeah.
[umm...]
I'm sorry, I don't think so.
[sigh]
[MACARON] (hmm...)
Nothing's happened.
Let's keep watching
just in case.
She's not safe out here.
[MACARON] Yeah, right.
You just don't like that
she's up there alone
with the manager‐ron.
[hmpf!]
Hey.
[ISUZU] (grrr)
[hmpf!]
[KOBORY] So much rain...
It's kind of unusual, isn't it?
At least, we can take a
little break right now.
Yeah, but we can't get visitors
if the park's rained out!
Hey, you're a water spirit,
aren't you, sweet stuff?
Stop the rain, mii!
I can't. All I can do is cute
little tricks like this.
[TIRAMY] Miiii!
Wonder what he's yelling about?
[WRENCH] Bad news! Bad news!
BAD NEWS! [panting]
[MOFFLE] What's wrong with you?
You're gonna rust!
It's the drainage system!
[WRENCH] Bucket o' bolts gave
out on me with all this rain.
If it keeps up, the underground
facilities are gonna flood!
[SEIYA] What?!
That's terrible!
We'd have to close down
for a month!
Why did these things have to
quit NOW of all times?
[WRENCH] Uh, boss?
We talked about this yesterday.
You told me to shut
one of 'em down.
[SEIYA] (gasp)
What'll we do if
something goes wrong?
So that must've made the
other two pumps work too hard.
[WRENCH] Yeah, I reckon.
[SEIYA] (hmm...)
We have to do something
about this, and fast!
[SEIYA] I know!
We'd better move all
the merchandise first.
No wait,
safety's more important.
Either way, we have to
stop it before it floods
or we'll be done before
we can even reopen.
[ISUZU]
We'll set up an emergency base.
[SEIYA] (huh?!)
[SEIYA] Sento!
Everything's ready.
Just come with me.
[wow...]
[ISUZU] We'll need fire
extinguishing pumps in
ten crucial locations.
This is the Music Theater.
We've got the pumps, Isuzu‐ron!
[ISUZU] Flood control units,
please continue the bucket relay
until the pumps arrive.
[MUSE] (ugh, oof)
[ISUZU] In the meantime,
use sandbags to prevent
more flooding.
Facilities Unit! We stopped the
4th corridor from goin' under!
Now head for the west side
of the 5th corridor.
[WRENCH] Ten‐four!
All the pumps have been set up.
Excellent.
Ready? Begin drainage!
[ALL] Roger!
[ASHE] Please begin drainage!
[CREW 1] Begin drainage!
[CREW 2] Begin drainage!
Ron!
Mii!
Now, let's do this!
[engine starting]
Th‐this is the Elementario Unit!
We've been keeping up the
bucket relay for a while now.
Could you please send us a pump
as soon as you can?
We can't afford to move
the pumps away from the
badly affected areas.
I'll send security over.
Go help them, Okuro.
[OKURO] Yes, ma'am!
Hold on for another 20 minutes.
[MUSE] (awwww!)
[TRIKEN] Miss Isuzu,
the unit's immobilized!
[ISUZU] Don't abandon your post.
If you do, I'll gun you down.
Hey, Ashe, let me take over here
while you go get everyone some
food and a place to rest.
[TRIKEN] Y‐yes, ma'am!
[ASHE] Yes, sir.
[TRIKEN]
I'm bowing in subordination!
[WRENCH] Facilities Unit to HQ,
the drainage system's
back in business!
Repeat, the drainage system's
[SYLPHY] (streeetch)
Message received.
[ASHE] (sigh of relief)
[ISUZU] (big sigh)
Well, good work.
[WRENCH]
Nah, I can't take the credit.
[ISUZU] (huh?)
[WRENCH] Good job,
Miss Former Manager.
[ISUZU] (huh?!)
[WRENCH] Well, I better get back
to work. Over and out.
[disconnect signal]
[ah!]
[SEIYA] No issues over here.
[ISUZU] Good.
Is this the of 'em?
That's right.
Look, Kanie...
[SEIYA] Uh‐huh?
I don't exactly have
a problem with you.
No?
The problem is with me,
actually.
Before this, I worked as
the acting manager of
Amagi Brilliant Park.
Since I was a soldier,
I thought I could solve every
problem with brute force.
"Soldier"?
I'm a member of the Royal Guard.
I grew up in
a military household,
so I never thought twice
about becoming a soldier.
I came here because
I was commanded to
re‐energize this park.
That's kind of a tall order,
isn't it?
Yes, it is.
And I knew that.
I knew I wasn't cut out for
a mission like this.
But...
I didn't want to disappoint
or dishonor my family,
so I did my best anyway.
And I failed.
[hmm] So I take it that was
your first big setback as
a member of the elite.
A setback? Perhaps.
Then, why didn't you
just run away
and forget what your family
wanted you to do?
[hmm?] Sento?
Run away?
That never even crossed my mind.
[SEIYA] Jeez...
Well, in any case,
I ended up failing.
And I couldn't decide how
to reconcile that fact
within myself.
[ISUZU] I know the cast members
all hate me now.
You know, I've been through
my share of setbacks too.
[ISUZU] (uh...)
Uh... [ahem...]
[SEIYA] The truth is
I'm afraid of heights.
[ISUZU] (huh?)
[SEIYA] Just when I was getting
popular as a child actor...
Well, I...
I just couldn't deal with
high places anymore.
It was kinda like your thing.
Maybe I was scared of making my
parents sad, or losing fans...
When I look back,
it doesn't make sense.
Being afraid of heights wasn't
the only reason or anything,
but I quit show business
around that time.
And of course they were
disappointed and yelled,
and the whole thing
caused a lot of problems.
It wasn't a fun time.
It sounds difficult.
But all of that aside...
My point is...
[ISUZU] (huh?)
[SEIYA] Those setbacks...
That's all they really are!
[ISUZU] (ah!)
That kind of stupid crap
happens to people every day!
If you're upset about
something like that,
then you're just weak!
Hear me?! Weak!
Right?!
What do you think about THAT?!
[ISUZU] (uh...)
[laughter]
I see...
[SEIYA] (continuing laughter)
Well then, I suppose that
means I'm weak.
I'm glad you understand.
Still, I never would've
expected you to tell me
about something so personal
as your fear of heights.
[huh?] Oh yeah, I did.
That's funny.
But why?
Oh well, now you know.
[CROWD] Hurray!
(laughing & celebrating)
[MUSE] Miss Isuzu!
[TIRAMY] That was amazing, mii!
[MACARON]
That's our Miss Isuzu‐ron!
[ISUZU] (huh?)
[MUSE] We're all tired,
but we wanted to take a
moment to say thank you!
[clapping]
Hey, weren't you trying to tell
me earlier that all the cast
members hated you?
How do you explain this?
[ah...]
[small chuckle]
Oh, I almost forgot!
I heard you rode on the
Ferris wheel with
Her Majesty yesterday.
Ah, uh...
So you know about that, huh?
[ISUZU] Macaron told me.
So? I assume you must've been
terrified of the height?
[ungh!] Don't go there.
[ISUZU] Does that mean
you've gotten over it?
Look, it's not important.
It is! I'm very interested.
[SEIYA] Just gimme a break.
[RUBRUM] (rumbling roar)
[ISUZU & SEIYA] Time for
the attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU] This is Elementario, the
home of the four nature spirits.
[SEIYA] Can't they use their
powers to make the show better?
[ISUZU] Not indoors. The flames
would set the place on fire,
water's difficult to clean up,
and they can't very well dig
holes through the floor.
[SEIYA]
What about Sylphy's wind magic?
[ISUZU] They use it sometimes,
but it's so drafty in there
during the winter,
it ends up making
the audience freeze.
[SEIYA] Then get it fixed!