We don't have enough staff!
Aw,moff! First, it was money,
now it's personnel?
But, sir, you only just
hired several new employees
a few days ago.
With no consideration for the
cost of paying them all,
I might add.
[urk!]
Okay, so we did hire
a few more people,
but that was only in that
one specialized area.
We just need more in general.
So, you're suggesting that
we do some new recruiting?
I'm not so sure about that.
Do you really think we'll
get enough applicants?
We won't know until we try.
There might be a whole flock
of beautiful girls
just dying to work here.
If that happens, I'll be bowing
down in gratitude.
Who knows, one of them might
even rival you, Miss Isuzu.
Possibly.
But if anyone who applies
is more suited for the
position than I am,
I'll gladly surrender my
post on the spot.
[ALL] Uh...
I'm sorry, Miss Isuzu,
that was a joke.
[ISUZU] (uh...)
Well, anyway, we can start
looking tomorrow.
That'll be all!
[GIRLS] Mr. Kanie!
[ah!]
You need a new secretary?
I can do it!
Pick me!
Huh?
(laughing)
[SEIYA] You're hired!
All of you start immediately!
[GIRLS] (giggling)
Wait a minute...
[SEIYA] I had a feeling
this interview process
would cause some pressure.
So you three just keep on
pressuring me, okay?
[grrr]
[GIRLS] (giggling)
Stop this right now!
It isn't professional!
[hmmm?] Oh, hey, Sento.
You're still here?
[gasp]
I don't need you anymore.
[gasp] No!
[gunshot]
[ah!] [huh?]
A dream?
Why would I dream
something like that?
You know, I've been through
my share of setbacks too.
If it gets us one more visitor,
then it's worth it!
I'm ready to do
whatever it takes.
I... well, uh...
I couldn't deal with
high places, not anymore.
[sigh]
[ummm] [nervous giggle]
[gasp]
[sigh]
[background chatter]
[MACARON] Whoa, I can't believe
you actually eat the curry here.
[ISUZU] (hmmm?)
Oh, good morning, Macaron.
Good morning, ron.
Don't tell me you really
like that garbage.
I don't know, I just felt like
having something else today.
Okay, it's your funeral.
One time, Wanipee‐ron
exploded out both ends
after eating that junk.
Mind if I sit here?
[ISUZU] Sure.
[ughhh...]
Curry for breakfast is
gonna make you fat.
That doesn't really concern me.
And you look like a pathetic
loner when you eat by yourself.
That doesn't concern me either.
Oh, come on, it's almost like
you're being boring on purpose!
[ISUZU] (huh?)
Let me guess: You're the kind of
person who overthinks everything
and gets all
word‐constipated, right?!
[ISUZU] (ah!)
[ISUZU]
That doesn't concern me either.
[sigh]
[MACARON]
Look, there's Kanie‐ron!
[thrumming]
[splut!]
Nevermind! That wasn't him.
[ISUZU] Oh...
[heh, heh]
Yes!
[students arriving at school]
Hey, wait up, Sento!
You seem kinda sad today.
Yes, I had a terrible dream,
breakfast tasted disgusting,
my colleague criticized me,
[GIRL] (hmmm?)
and my job's going as
badly as it possibly can.
Oh, wow,
that sounds pretty tough.
Of course it is!
And I'm supposed to be
assisting Kanie with his work,
but what if I'm not
meeting his expectations?
I'm so afraid he
might decide to‐ [ah!]
Wait, did you say "Kanie"?
What's he got to‐
What's wrong, Sento?
[mmmm] I have to go!
[GIRL] (huh?)
Whoa!
[MOFFLE] One, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two...
And finish!
Only Sylphy got it
right, as usual.
Back to one!
[THREE] Aww...
No way, mii!
How did you get Isuzu to
swallow a ponesty bean?!
I snuck it into her food
this morning.
But, Macaron, I only gave you
that bean because you told me
you wanted to find out how
your daughter really feels
about you, mii!
I thought you were gonna try
to get custody back from
your ex‐wife, remember?
Oh yeah, that's still the plan.
But I wanted to test it on
Isuzu‐ron first, in case
it's dangerous.
Ooh, you ARE bad!
Poor Isuzu must be spilling
her guts all over the
place today, mii!
Too bad she went off to school
before I could see what kinda
funny stuff it made her say.
Aw man, that's a bummer!
Dude, if it were me,
I would've asked her how many
times a week she slaps the flap!
[MACARON] You're so nasty!
[BOTH] (giggling)
If you asked her
something like that,
she'd blow your brains out!
[clack]
[ISUZU] Don't worry about that.
[BOTH] (ah!) (uuuhhhh....)
If you want, I'll get it
over with right now!
[BOTH] (WAAAHHH!!!)
[gunshots]
What did you do now?
[panting]
[ISUZU] I had to.
They slipped me a ponesty bean
so they could ask me
inappropriate questions.
Inappropriate?
Like how many times a week‐
[mmff!]
Just forget it!
I still don't understand,
but whatever.
As soon as you clean up
all the bodies,
could you meet me in the
administration building?
We're starting the
interviews at 1.
[ISUZU] (ah!) I forgot?!
What? Do you have a
problem with that?
I have several
problems with that!
I can't keep from
speaking my mind!
I'm scared I might accidentally
reveal these strange feelings
I have for you‐
ah!] [mmmm!]
[SEIYA] Are you okay there?
[ISUZU] Of course I'm not!
Let me call in sick!
If I stay here, you might find
out how I fee‐ [mmmmphf!]
[argh!] [argh!]
You look like you've got
plenty of energy to me, Sento.
Anyway, don't be late.
[ah!]
[JIRO] (forced laugh)
Well, y'see folks, I didn't
do so hot in the mayoral
election the other day,
so I was hoping I could just
work here until I find myself
and maybe shoot for
prime minister next time.
Good luck with that!
He's so determined.
[SEIYA] Yeah, we could hire him.
[MOFFLE]
Are you moffin' serious?!
[SEIYA] I figure somebody
who's that resilient
is less likely
to walk out on us.
Moff...
[PITCHER] (waaahh!)
Why? WHY did I decide
to make that stupid pitch
in the very last inning?!
I'm so ashamed!
And how does that
make you qualified?
High school athletes DO create
some interesting drama.
Okay, let's hire him.
[MOFFLE] What?!
Cast members are expected
to be entertaining for
the guests, right?
Moff...
I was recently fired from my job
as a professional wrestler.
See, I've always been
a little sensitive.
So I didn't really like doing
wrestling techniques on people.
I mean, I never wanted
to hurt anybody.
A wrestler who doesn't wrestle.
But Okuro in security is
already a masked man.
And we can't have two.
THAT'S what you
have a problem with?!
You mean, I don't get the job?
Well, you could take it off.
I refuse!
[MOFFLE] That was sudden!
Sorry, but you look
too similar to a character
we already have on the payroll.
I would rather die
than remove my mask!
[SEIYA] (grrr)
We need to get Okuro in here.
[BING!]
[BOTH] (ungh...)
[SEIYA] I thought you
couldn't hurt anybody?
[ISUZU] His pro‐wrestler
instincts took over.
[SEIYA] Hired.
Didn't know the requirements
were literally just living
and breathing.
I told you we were desperate
for new hires, stupid rat.
I am the legendary
shadow of Iga,
prepared to lay down my life
for my lord at any time.
[SEIYA] Hired.
Earth is mostly water‐
[COUNTDOWN] Five... four...
[SEIYA] Hired!
Hayoooooooooooooo!!
[SEIYA] Hired.
[EIKO] Excuse me.
[GONG!]
My name is Eiko Adachi.
Thank you for taking the
time to see me today.
She's normal!
And I was starting to think all
of them would be crazy people.
[gasp!]
She...
She was in my dream!
[hmm?]
[uhhh...]
Uh, right, let's see,
Eiko Adachi...
Oh, it says here you used to
work with a talent agency,
and that you've performed
in a few films.
Can you tell us a little bit
about the kind of movies
you've starred in?
Sure! I did AV.
That's pretty cool.
Wait, what?
[MOFFLE] (huh?!)
I did AV.
[BOTH] (wah!)
[ISUZU] (grrr)
I see...
Uh, did you do a lot of those?
Oh, no, I only ever worked
on about ten films.
Only ten films?!
Right.
[MOFFLE] Moff!
[MOFFLE] She did adult video?!
Ask for her stage name!
I'm not asking her for that!
For what?
[SEIYA] Ah, nothing!
Nothing at all!
Sorry about that, we were
just a little surprised
by your unusual
work history, that's all.
I get that all the time,
to tell you the truth.
So please don't worry.
I'm used to it by now.
Uh, so glad to hear that...
Why are YOU sweating? She's the
one who's getting interviewed!
Now hurry up and ask her
what her porn name is!
Quit acting like such a creep!
Moff, moff...
[small giggle]
[deep breath]
S‐Sento, what should we do?
[ISUZU] (grrr)
[SEIYA] (ungh!)
Do not rely on me
for advice today, Kanie!
I am a mess right now!
I'm sitting here about
to die from shock
because that woman looks
just like the one from the
nightmare I had last night!
And here you are getting
all excited about her
adult video career!
I understand that she's got
bigger breasts than I do,
and that she looks like one of
those mature, comforting types
and that her level of sexual
experience is probably
off the charts,
but you don't even know her!
Don't tell me! You're thinking
about making her your new
[gasp!] [mmmphf!]
[mmmphf!] [mmmphf!] [mmmphf!]
Uh, Sento?
So, why did you apply?
Uh, oh, yeah, good question.
Could you tell us why
you're interested in
working at our park?
Well, to be perfectly
honest with you,
I wasn't very good
at my last job.
Although it was satisfying.
[BOTH] Satisfying?!
But then I decided it would be
a lot more fulfilling
if I could see it with my own
eyes when the customers
enjoy the work I do.
Oh, but that isn't much of
a reason, now is it?
Oh, no, I think it's a
perfectly good reason actually.
[MOFFLE] (um‐hmm, um‐hmm)
So why did she come HERE?
Who cares!
You've been hired.
[EIKO] Thank you very much!
[phone alert]
So, what's that about?
Moff, I sent Triken
a picture of Eiko Adachi
so he could track her down.
He's kind of a porn expert.
Oh,I see, that's interesting.
Anyway, who we got next?
He found it?
[MOFFLE] Found what?
[ummm]
You know, uh,
did he find out the...
Oh, yeah, he figured out her
stage name and everything.
You're so nasty.
[SEIYA] (ah!) Look...
[door opening]
[BIINO] I'm sorry I'm late!
Hi there!
My name's Biino Bando.
Thank you for seeing me today!
[ISUZU] Again?!
She was there too!
[hmm] She seems enthusia‐
Uh, Ms. Bando?
[BIINO] Yes, sir?
[SEIYA] Are you bleeding?
[BIINO] Oh, sorry about that,
I was in such a rush.
[SEIYA] Are you okay?!
Of course, I'm fine!
It's nothing but a scratch!
I promise!
[SEIYA] (ah!) Uhhh...
[MOFFLE] Moff!
Looks like a stab wound.
I'd say she's lost about a
liter's worth of blood so far.
[SEIYA] She needs help!
No really,
I don't need any help.
I'm putting everything on the
line for this interview...
[ungh...]
It's not worth your life!
Trust me!
[BIINO] No, I'll die
before I give this up... [hack]
All right, fine, you're hired!
You've got the job!
Now, please let me call an
ambulance before you die!
[panting]
[BOTH] (ah!)
[SEIYA] Who is this guy?!
He's my older brother.
[SEIYA] Your older brother?!
[BIINO] He said he didn't want
me to take on a part time job.
He wanted to stop me from coming
to the interview, so he‐
[SEIYA]
I'm really worried about you...
What do you think
we should do with him?
You got the job!
[SEIYA] No way!
[BROTHER] (wah!) (hyah!)
[splat!]
Hey, control your brother!
[grrr]
[gunshot]
Moff!
[BROTHER] (arrgghh!)
[unfffh!]
[splat!]
He's gonna be eating through
a tube from now on.
[MOFFLE] I wonder if we're
gonna regret hiring that one?
[SHIINA] Um...
I think we made
the right choice.
I know it's not normally
rational to hire someone
after an interview
goes that badly,
but she had the incredible
composure and fortitude
to keep smiling despite
having just been stabbed,
and I believe the park
could benefit from that.
[SEIYA] Hmm...
What's wrong?
Nothing, I think what
you're saying makes sense.
[SHIINA] Um...
But if you're really that
good at deciding what's
best for AmaBri,
maybe you should take a look
at your own behavior while
you're at it, huh?
[huh?!]
[MOFFLE] If only your brain
was as big as your boobs.
[grrr] Now you're both dead!
[BOTH]
THAT'S what we're talking about!
[SHIINA] (squeal)
[SEIYA] (hmm?)
Wait a second; who's that?
E‐E‐E‐Excuse me!
[ISUZU] (huh?!)
[gasp] She was in my dream too!
Dream? What the heck is
going on with you today?
[huh?] I'm perfectly fine.
Anyway,
this is the last applicant.
Isn't that the
Amagi High uniform?
Y‐Yes! M‐M‐My name's
Sh‐Sh‐Shiina Chujo!
U‐um, the reason I wanted t‐t‐to
work here is b‐because I‐
[SEIYA] Stop panicking!
[SHIINA] (ah! I‐I'm s‐sorry...
[sigh] So, what do you think?
I think she'll do.
We didn't end up hiring
very many girls today.
And she doesn't look like the
type who'd try to seduce y
[mmmphf!]
[SHIINA] (huh?) (ah!)
[ISUZU] [mmmphf!] [mmmphf!]
Moff, I'm not sure if she'd
be okay talking to guests
with a scaredy‐cat
personality like that.
But sure, let's give her a shot.
And here I was expecting you
to turn this one down.
After all the circus freaks
we've seen today,
I don't think I care anymore.
Good point.
Well,
I guess that settles it then.
Shiina Chujo, welcome aboard.
[aahhhh!]
Th‐thank you so much, sir!
I appreciate it!
[hmpf]
[SEIYA]
That should be all of it.
[stretch]
[hmm?] Need something?
[ISUZU] What you said before...
[SEIYA] Before?
Macaron said something
like that today too.
He says that I overthink things
and get tongue‐tied.
[hmmm?]
[ISUZU] I've never been
very good at interacting with
other people face‐to‐face.
[SEIYA] Hence, the gun.
[ISUZU] That's right.
If I'm the one who's in control,
then I can think about
the situation logically.
Technically, I criticized your
judgement of character,
not your ability to
talk to people.
[ISUZU] (ah!) (huh?)
[SEIYA]
So quit moping around, jeez.
I suppose this is your
backhanded way of
cheering me up?
Cheering you up?
Why would I do that?
[ISUZU] (sigh)
I'm envious of you in more
ways than one, you know.
To me, Kanie, you're very‐
[mphf!] [mphf!] [mphf!]
[SEIYA] Not that again!
Don't feel bad.
I can totally understand
[ISUZU] (panting)
you being jealous of
my superior genius.
Don't you think you ought
to do something about the way
you always talk down to everyone
as though you're better
than they are?
But that's the thing.
I AM better than everybody else.
What do you expect me to do?
Goddess Libra, please unleash
your wrath on this wretched man.
[SEIYA] What did you say?
None of your business.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'd better go.
[satisfied sigh]
Hmm...
She was acting like
such a weirdo today.
[phone buzz]
Huh...
What's with that emoji?
[MACARON] What a dumbass, ron!
How could anybody
mistake this...
for THIS?!
I guess the aspect ratio
got moffed up
when I sent Triken
that picture.
We might as well
watch it anyway, mii!
No way!
Yeah, not my thing.
Eh, I can dig it.
[huh?]
[BOTH] (wah?!)
[TIRAMY] (giggling)
[BOTH] (UGGHHH!)
[nervous breath]
[gasp]
[EIKO]
Aw, look, it's a baby lamb!
[LAMB] (bleating)
It's amazing the way it sucks
and sucks on its mother's nipple
for dear life!
[ISUZU] (uuhhh...)
[EIKO]
And look at those kittens!
They love drinking
their mother's milk!
Next, we have piglets.
Oh my goodness, they're
fighting over their mommy!
[ISUZU]
Oh, so AV means "animal video".
[EIKO] Isn't that sweet?
[ALL] (wow!)
[SHIINA] It's Moffle!
[JIRO] The famous trio!
[ALL] (ah!)
Shut your pieholes!
And don't look so happy.
I want you maggots
in a straight line!
Listen up, punks!
From this day forward,
you are no longer human beings.
You are lower than scum!
Do you understand me?!
We're gonna beat you senseless
with everything you need to know
about excellent
customer service, ron!
There's nothing more
satisfying to us than
watching you losers break down
and cry after you fail, mii!
Lesson Number One:
The first and last words
out of your mouth are "sir!"
You got that?
[ALL] S‐Sir! Yes, sir!
I can't hear you!
[ALL] (wahh!)
I want you to say it
loud and clear! Say it!
[ALL] Sir, yes, sir!
[TIRAMY] Not loud enough!
You sound like a bunch of
wussy little girls!
You better learn to‐ [oofff!]
Stop scaring them!
What's gonna happen
if all of them quit?!
[MOFFLE] Perfect timing.
I'll make an example outta you!
Somebody needs to cut you
down to size, rat face!
[gunshot]
[BOTH] (arrgghhh!)
[ISUZU] No fighting.
[ALL] (gasp)
Does anyone have questions?
[ALL] (gah!) (um‐um!)
[ISUZU & SEIYA] Time for
the attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU]
Today we have Tomb Ranger,
the crowd‐favorite
attraction of Wild Valley.
[ISUZU] Visitors are invited to
join Jack Randy on a Wild West
treasure‐hunting adventure.
[SEIYA] Oh, one of those
exploration‐type rides.
Those are fun.
What's the story like?
[ISUZU] You fight pirates.
[SEIYA] Uh...
[ISUZU] It's set in Japan.
[SEIYA] What?
[ISUZU] And the treasure
is miso rice crackers.
[SEIYA] Wait, how is
that a Wild West adventure?!