[deep thrumming]
[urk]
[ISUZU] I know it's sudden,
Seiya Kanie, but...
Are you free next Sunday?
I want to go to a theme park
together with you.
[confused stammer, gulp]
Is this your way of asking me
on a date or something?
[ISUZU] Sure.
And why are you packing heat?
[ISUZU]
To keep you from running.
You'll shoot if I say no?
[ISUZU] Correct. Your answer?
Look, you can't expect me to‐
[shot fired]
[nervous gulp]
[ISUZU] Kanie...
[wah!]
Answer me.
[nervous gulp]
Mm‐hm!
How's it going today, handsome?
[BOY] Hey check out that weirdo.
Lookin' good as usual.
[BOY 2] Looks like he's checking
himself out.
Since I AM a total stud
[BOY 2] Probably just a jerk.
AND I'm one of the smartest
students in the school,
[BOY] What a loser.
the fact that I was
asked out on a date
[GUY] Did say he's a stud?
by some transfer student I've
never spoken to before,
[GIRL] Ugh, that's gross.
just doesn't surprise me.
[gah!]
Let's go.
[SEIYA] O‐okay...
[SEIYA] Isuzu Sento...
[ISUZU] That's my name.
[SEIYA]
Where exactly are we going?
[ISUZU] AmaBri.
[SEIYA] "AmaBri"?
[ISUZU] Amagi Brilliant Park.
There's a bus that goes
straight to it from here.
[SEIYA] See ya.
[urk!]
Mommy!
That pretty lady's got
blue stripes on her panties.
Look over there!
Just be like everybody else and
pretend like you don't see it.
So if I don't come with you,
I'm dead?
That's the idea.
What's so great about this
amusement park anyway?
To put it more clearly,
it's a theme park.
What's the difference?
And besides,
don't you think you owe me an
explanation for all of this?
It hasn't been that long since
you transferred to our school,
and you're trying this hard
to get a date?
I mean I know
I'm devilishly good‐looking,
but there's gotta be
some other reason!
What are you trying
to accomplish here?
Why does it have to be THAT
specific park of all places?
Did you pull that out of your‐
[SEIYA]
Amagi Brilliant Park, huh?
Have you ever been there
before, Kanie?
I think I might've been to it
one time when I was
really little,
but I'm not sure if I...
[SEIYA] Doesn't look that bad.
[bus chime]
[PA]
Next stop, Amagi Brilliant Park.
I repeat,
Amagi Brilliant Park.
[ISUZU] Wait.
[PA]
Please take all your belongings
It's the next one.
[PA] and watch your step
as you exit the bus.
Then what's that big,
fancy castle thing?
A love hotel.
Oh...
WHAT?!
A love hotel.
Yeah, I get it!
It's a common mistake.
The main park entrance
used to be at that stop,
until the park was renovated
ten years ago.
The love hotel was built on
that land shortly after that.
[gulp] That's misleading!
Why don't they just change
the name of the bus stop then?
That request was made
a while ago,
but it keeps getting put off
for some reason.
Despite how many guests
get off the bus back there.
Wait, "guests"?
You know, customers.
That's what they're called
at most theme parks.
The customers are guests,
and the staff are
called cast members.
Try to remember that.
Isuzu Sento,
you're kind of a strange girl,
you know that?
[ISUZU] Here we are, Kanie.
[ugh]
[desolate wind blowing]
[SEIYA]
It's this dead on a Sunday?
[ISUZU]
Typical count on weekend days is
two thousand one hundred ten.
That's precise.
[ISUZU] Let's go to
Sorcerer's Hill first.
"Sorcerer's Hill"?
[ISUZU]
It's one of the areas of AmaBri.
Since it's home to the
lovable mascot characters
of the magical kingdom
of Maple Land,
it's bursting with
dreams and happiness.
[SEIYA]
The way you said that just now
makes me think it's bursting
with boredom.
[ISUZU] This is
Tiramy's Flower Adventure.
Tiramy's a flower fairy.
I'd like to recommend climbing
aboard the Fancy Train.
It'll whisk you away to a
delightful world full of
love and cheer.
[SEIYA]
Like I told you the first time,
you're not making it sound
very delightful at all.
Welcome...
Two, please.
[ATTENDANT] Sure.
[gah!]
Seems the rails are misaligned.
That's dangerous!
[ISUZU] I quite agree.
[FLOWERS]
Weeelcome to Tiiiiramy's
Floooweerrrr Adventuuuure!
[SEIYA] What the...
This is the part where Tiramy's
supposed to come out
and wave at everyone.
But he's missing again.
[SEIYA] Again?
Wait a minute,
how many times have you
been to this place?
So, how was that?
Oh, God...
[ISUZU] Next we have
Macaron's Music Theater.
He's a music fairy.
Macaron's performances feature
sweet melodies and
uplifting rhythms.
It's guaranteed to make your
heart sing with delight.
[SEIYA] We need to have
a talk about this.
[ISUZU] He only works
when he feels like it.
That's an artist for you.
Seriously?!
[ISUZU]
This is Moffle's Sweets House.
Moffle is a sweets fairy as well
as the most popular mascot.
Just one bite of these treats
and you'll be floating through
a world of bliss.
[SEIYA] Oh, come on!
[CHEERFUL PA] Welcome to
Moffle's Sweets House!
Uh‐oh, the shop is full
of mischievous mice!
Use the magic water guns
to teach them a lesson!
So it's some kind of
shooting game?
All I have to do is shoot
the mice with this gun?
Correct.
[SEIYA] Hmph!
I'm a pro at these
kinds of games.
Get ready to marvel at
the work of a true master.
[CHEERFUL PA]
Let the slaughter begin!
Did she say "slaughter"?!
[mouse squeaks]
[SEIYA] (ah!)
They're fast!
I got one!
We're headed for the pantry.
Don't let your guard down.
This game is
freaking impossible!
Just try harder.
Okay, that was...
WAY too hard...
[CHEERFUL PA] Aww, darn!
You didn't kill very many!
Wait! I was killing them?!
But you said I was just
teaching them a lesson!
[ISUZU]
Right, the more mice you kill,
the bigger the reward
you can get for their corpses.
Do you even realize how
violent you sound right now?
Family‐friendly places like this
aren't supposed to use words
like "kill" or "corpses."
[CHEERFUL PA] But Moffle
appreciates all your help!
Be sure to take a photo with him
in the next room before you go!
This is the room where you get
your picture taken with Moffle.
[SEIYA] I don't really care
to take pictures
with a guy in a rat suit
or whatever.
[ISUZU] Just say hello.
It'll be fun, I promise.
Are you telling me
there are people
who find this crazy
death game FUN?
[ISUZU] Of course.
Those are photos of
all the guests
who have gotten high scores
in the past.
[SEIYA] Looks like it appeals to
a specific kind of person.
[door creaking]
[MOFFLE] Moff!
[ISUZU]
Moffle, the sweets fairy.
He's the most popular
mascot here.
Huh...
Something wrong?
No...
He just irks me for some reason.
We'd like to take a photo
with you, all right?
[MOFFLE] Moff.
Wait, what's the point
if you're not in it?!
[MOFFLE] (tch!)
Why are you copping
an attitude?!
I'm a customer, buddy!
Try to calm down, Kanie.
Right...
Don't worry, I can be calm.
I promise I won't lose my cool.
Whatever, I'm out.
I'm not gonna sit here
and take this crap from
a knockoff like‐ [gah!]
There's nothing Moffle
despises more than being
called a knockoff.
Oh, so that makes it okay
to throw a camera
at a customer's head?!
Why's he standing there like
he's ready to punch me out?!
Wahhhhahah!
All right, that's it.
NOW I'm angry! [gaaah!]
[SEIYA, MOFFLE] (ooofff!)
[ISUZU] That's better.
[SEIYA]
That crazy woman just shot me!
She actually shot me!
Am I really gonna die
because of some stupid guy
in a mascot suit?!
I lived...
You two were about to engage
in a fight to the death.
And I won't allow you to sully
the Sweets House of happiness
with your blood.
[SEIYA] I don't see any
happiness in here!
And besides, you've got
no right to talk,
Little Miss Sharpshooter!
Right. Well, Kanie,
did you have a good time
bonding with Moffle
through friendly competition?
[SEIYA] Is THAT what
you're calling it?!
You'll get along, right?
[SEIYA] No way!
Took the words
right out of my mouth.
Wait a second, he talks too?
[ISUZU]
Well, that's enough for now.
We got our souvenir photo,
so let's get moving.
We got what?
[groan]
[SEIYA] That sucked!
He's a total jerk!
You really think so?
[SEIYA] Why does this park need
an angry mouse character
wearing a goofy hat?
Seriously, the guy inside the
suit must have some kind of
attitude problem.
There's nobody inside the suit.
[SEIYA] 'Scuse me?
It's only Moffle.
There's nobody inside the suit.
Oh, right, I get it now.
You're supposed to
tell everybody
it's a real magical mouse thing
instead of a guy in a suit
so the kids don't stop believing
in Santa Claus or whatever.
Is that what's going on?
[ISUZU] No, I'm saying there's
no one inside the suit.
Moffle is a real resident of
the magical kingdom.
"Magical kingdom"?
All right, you win,
if it means that much to you.
[ISUZU]
This is the Elementario Theatre.
Here, the four elemental spirits
perform beautifully
choreographed dance numbers
and unbelievable wire stunts.
My name is Muse,
the water spirit! (giggle)
We hope you enjoy the
Elementario spectacular!
You can call me Sylphy.
I'm the spirit of wind.
You wanna be friends?
I'm the earth spirit known as
Kobory.
Uhmm...
it's lovely to meet you.
What's up?
I'm Salama.
I'm the fire spirit.
All right, having fun?!
[SYLPHY] (giggling) (whoooo!)
Wow, it sure
sounds like you are!
[SYLPY] (giggling)
[MUSE] Let's get
this show on the road!
[SULPHY] (whoooo!)
This is sad.
[ISUZU]
That's about how it always is.
Let's continue the tour.
[ISUZU]
The Thrill Coaster...
A heart‐pounding adventure
aboard a speeding train
of fun and thrills.
Are you scared?
[SEIYA] You've gotta be joking.
[ISUZU] Good, let's take a ride.
Were you terrified?
[SEIYA] Not really.
Oh, well, let's keep moving.
[ISUZU] Brilliant Market...
Check out AmaBri's
hottest merchandise.
[SEIYA] This place
looks really outdated.
[ISUZU] Kiddie Play...
A spacious play area
glowing with the smiles
of children.
[SEIYA] Obviously.
[ISUZU] Free Fall...
They slowed it down
so it wouldn't scare the
little kids too much.
[SEIYA] So it's an elevator.
[ISUZU] The Coffee Cups...
They're famous for
their extreme speed.
[SEIYA]
I think I'm gonna puke...
I hate this!
Seems like you're upset.
Why wouldn't I be?
Every single attraction
in this park
is a lame piece of crap!
Nothing works right,
the service is terrible...
At least the love hotel
LOOKS nice!
And the worst part of it is
the people running this place
don't know the first thing
about entertainment!
Do they really think kids are
fooled by stupid gags like this?
Kids are a lot harder to trick
than you might think!
It's not something you can
just pull out of your ass!
You have to work hard
and commit to it!
But no, this place doesn't even
come CLOSE to that!
If they want to
make dreams come true,
the people who work here have to
believe in their own dreams
first!
I mean‐ (uh...)
(sigh)
If you want to make
dreams come true,
then the first thing you
have to do is believe
in dreams yourself.
You said it harshly,
but you're right.
But that doesn't sound like
something your normal everyday
high school student would say.
Just forget it.
I copied it from a book.
You know, at first, I assumed
that the reason you were
acting so irritated
was because a strange girl
forced you to come to
a theme park
and wander around
with her all day.
(hmph) So you DO know
you're being a huge
inconvenience to me then.
But you're obviously frustrated
because of another issue
entirely, aren't you?
It's like you're angry
at the park itself.
Seiya Kanie... Amagi High School
Class 2‐4, age 16.
Currently resides with his aunt.
How did you know that?
[ISUZU] Attractive, intelligent,
superior athletic skills.
True, but what's your point?
[ISUZU] A man of many talents.
Can succeed at almost anything,
but notoriously narcissistic.
[SEIYA] Hm?
[ISUZU] Loves himself
so much it's disgusting.
[SEIYA] Whoa!
[ISUZU] That's why you don't
have friends or a girlfriend.
Hey, wait! (uh...)
[ISUZU] You always
eat your lunch by yourself
because no one likes you.
(aaaaghhhh!)
Where did you get all this
info about my life?
I've been doing
extensive research.
Okay, but WHY did you do
all that research?!
Seiya Kodama...
[SEIYA] (gasp)
From what I've heard,
there was a successful child
actor by that name
a few years ago.
Any adult would've called him
the perfect child.
But for whatever reason,
Seiya Kodama suddenly retired
five years ago.
[ISUZU] He should be in
high school by now, right?
What do you think he would say
if he saw this place?
(small sigh)
Now I get it...
You made me come here
because you knew about that
from the start.
That's correct.
Look, I don't know what it is
you're trying to pull here,
but Seiya Kodama's been dead
for a long time, all right?
He disappeared.
So if you think you can use him
to your advantage somehow,
then you're wasting your time.
That's it.
Try to shoot me if you want,
but I'm outta here.
[ISUZU] Wait!
You have to eat these
before you go.
They'll be cold soon.
I don't care about
your croquettes.
[ISUZU] Just eat them, please.
The crust isn't very thick,
but the crunch is exquisite.
The inside is juicy and warm.
Plus, the minced meat and
mashed potatoes make a
perfect combo of flavors!
[ISUZU] Do you like them?
(ah!)Yeah...
Those are exclusive
to this park.
You can't get them
anywhere else.
Wow, did you make these?
I didn't.
But would you like to meet
the one who did?
[gates groaning]
[SEIYA] How are you affiliated
with this park?
[ISUZU] Did I say I was?
[SEIYA]
No, I just kinda figured it out.
Where are we going?
To the roof of Maple Castle.
You said you wanted to meet
the park manager.
I did?
[ISUZU] Kanie?
[SEIYA] (huh?)
Something wrong?
Uh, no, I'm okay.
Good...
Then you should go say hello
to Her Highness.
Huh?
[ISUZU] Go on.
Hello, you must be
Sir Seiya Kanie.
Uh, that's me.
I'm pleased to meet you.
My name is Latifah Fullanza.
And I happen to be the
manager of this park.
Manager?
Yes, I do so appreciate
you taking the time
to come and visit
our grounds today.
Uh, sure.
So you're the one who made
those croquettes?
[LATIFAH]
Oh, yes, I make them every day.
I like to do what I can
to help our guests enjoy
themselves here.
Um, don't take this the wrong
way, but what is it you want?
And who exactly are you?
The park is quite expansive.
Have you already seen all of it?
Uh‐huh, more than I wanted to.
[LATIFAH] What did you think?
Well, where do I start?
Say no more, I'm certain it
was far from ideal.
(sigh)
Sir Kanie...
[SEIYA] (huh?)
Please grant me this one favor.
Our precious park is
in danger of closing down,
and I was hoping that you
could be the one to rescue it.
What?
Amagi Brilliant Park
needs your leadership.
Please say you'll
be the manager for us!
You mean you want me
to be in charge of this place?
[LATIFAH] Yes...
You have what it takes to
save this park from ruin.
That is what the Oracle
has made clear to us.
[SEIYA] "Oracle"?
[LATIFAH] That's right.
We are residents of Maple Land,
a kingdom of magic.
Are you serious?
Yes. You see,
the kingdom where I was born
is different from the
world you live in,
because magical happenings
tend to be commonplace.
To tell you the truth,
most of the cast members
who live and work here at
Amagi Brilliant Park
are actually native to that
magical land the same as I am.
Huh?
However, if we don't succeed
in welcoming 250,000 visitors,
then the park will close
in three months.
If that happens, the people
of Maple Land will have
nowhere left to go,
which means we will cease
to exist forever.
Wait a second, you can't just
expect me to believe all this
magic stuff is real.
I understand this is difficult.
That's why I...
That's why I'm going to
demonstrate a bit of magic
for you right now, all right?
[SEIYA] Magic?
[LATIFAH] Indeed.
[ah!]
Now, Sir Kanie,
I need you to stay still please.
[SEIYA] (huh?)
[LATIFAH] Oh no, Sir Kanie!
Are you hurt?!
Please help me, Lady Isuzu!
We must move him
inside at once!
Sir Kanie, wake up!
Oh, I'm in my room?
Better wash up.
[ISUZU] [oh!]
[SEIYA] (wah! panting)
[SEIYA] Hey, Aunt Aisu!
I know you're in there!
Open up, I need to talk to you!
Aunt Aisu! Come out, hurry!
[ISUZU] (ugh)
What in the world
do you want at this hour?
[SEIYA] Aunt Aisu,
why is that girl here?!
Oh, you mean Isuzu?
She brought you home last night
after the last train was gone
so I let her stay.
I think she told me you tripped
and knocked yourself out.
Can't believe Seiya
had a date with a girl.
He's really changed his ways.
[SEIYA] (gah!)
Not that long ago, he thought
of every girl he met
as his nemesis.
Well, as his guardian,
I have to say I'm pleased.
That was really weird.
[AISU] Huh?
Did you say something just now?
Something about me
changing my ways?
[ISUZU] (ah!)
What?! Nothing!
Wh‐what are you talking about?!
It looked like you had
your mouth closed,
but I know I heard your voice.
[AISU] Oh, that's right!
I must be really
hungover right now!
I should probably go
back to sleep for a while.
And you'd better be getting
ready for school,
don't you think?
See ya!
Kanie!
[SEIYA] (wah!)
It would appear that you've just
awakened to a magic ability.
Huh?!
I assume you believe
what I told you now?
[SEIYA] (uuuhhh...)
[ISUZU & SEIYA] Time for
the attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU] This segment will
showcase all the exciting
attractions AmaBri has to offer.
[SEIYA] You don't sound excited.
[ISUZU] Our first feature is
Moffle's Sweets House.
The difficulty is
actually adjustable.
[SEIYA] It is?
[ISUZU] Easy, Normal, Hard,
and for the toughest
challengers, Insane.
Insane is so brutal that some
guests lose their senses.
[SEIYA]
I wouldn't advertise that.
[ISUZU] Oh, and Kanie, you
played on Easy this time.
[SEIYA] Easy?!