[bright music playing]
[water splashing]
[laughing & giggling]
[LITTLE GIRL]
I want some ice cream!
[happiness & fun]
[BIINO] Hope you enjoy it!
Strawberry's the best kind!
Moff!
[excited children]
Moff! Moff, moff, moff!
[ON SPEAKER] Wow, did you
hear that, boys and girls?
Moffle wants to thank every
one of you for coming out
to AmaBri today! (giggle)
[continued excitement]
Ron, ron, rooooon!
[EIKO ON SPEAKER]
Macaron wants to play!
Mii, mii, miiiiii!
[EIKO ON SPEAKER]
Tiramy's happy too!
[ON SPEAKER] Here we go!
[popping]
[excited cherring]
[SEIYA]
Still not enough turnout.
Okay, then we're just gonna have
to kick the entertainment
factor up another notch.
[huh?]
[ISUZU] That's what we're
here for, isn't it?
Definitely.
Don't screw up.
[umm]
What's wrong?
[SEIYA] Nothing.
[children laughing]
Look! I see Moffle!
[MOFFLE] Moff! Moff...
[LITTLE GIRL] Wow! (giggles)
[LITTLE BOY] (giggles)
I wanna go get
a closer look at him!
[LITTLE BOY] (mm‐hm!)
[LITTLE GIRL] (huh?)
[LITTLE BOY] (hmm?) A shark?
I wonder if he's
part of the show too?
[ominous music]
[roar]
[BOTH] (uuuhhh...)
[BOTH] (WAAHHHH!!!)
[SEIYA]
Why would you do that, Jaw?
I thought I told you to
always stay behind the scenes!
I apologize, sir!
Really, I do!
But I am a man of the sea!
And so I assumed that the pool
was the most appropriate place
for me to greet‐ (urk!)
Well, yeah, it wouldn't be a
problem if you could be tiny and
adorable all the time,
but whenever you get wet...
(waahh!)
[SEIYA]
You've never seen yourself?!
[JAW] (uhuhuh...)
[SEIYA] Ah, just go
hide in the machine room!
[JAW] (sobbing]
[JAW] I'm a disgrace.
I always thought it was my
destiny to live at sea,
and now...
[awkward laugh]
[alarm]
[BOTH] (huh?)
[BOTH] (aahhh!)
[ominous music]
[SHIINA] Umm...
[JAW]
What in Neptune's name is this?
Oh, this is actually a magic
portal that connects AmaBri
directly to Maple Land.
[GENJURO]
When the park was first built,
this gate was set up so we
could easily transport supplies.
[SHIINA] M‐M‐Maple Land, that's
the m‐m‐magical k‐k‐kingdom
all of you used to l‐l‐live in,
isn't that r‐right?
Yeah, exactly.
But then we decided to have
the portal sealed shut
since we don't really have any
use for it anymore, you know?
Oh hey,
there's water leaking out.
[ALL] (hmm...)
[GENJURO] Well anyway,
I'll get the Facilities guys
to come take a look at it.
You two keep an eye on it, okay?
[JAW] (uh...)
[rumble]
[BOTH] (huh?)
[water bursting]
[BOTH] (WAAAHHH!!)
[kids playing & laughing]
[canon shot]
[ISUZU] Aye, this be good land.
So me crew 'n' I'll be
takin' it fer ourselves!
Now, all ye filthy bilgerats
better take heed to what
we tell ye to do!
And if'n ye won't listen,
you'll answer to ME,
the Dread Lady Pirate,
Captain Isuzulha!
[KIDS] (huh?) What happened?
[ISUZU] Waa ha ha ha...
Ah,
she's moffin' terrible at this.
Avast, ye faithful crew!
Whoever makes a fuss
is walkin' the plank!
[ALL]
Aye aye, Captain! (giggles)
[BRATS] (aha!)
[ISUZU] (OM surprised)
[ON SPEAKER] Moffle says:
[MOFFLE] Moff moff moff moff!
We won't go easy on you,
pirates!
[MACARON] Ron! Ron!
[TIRAMY] Mii! Mii!
[MOFFLE] Moff! Moff!
[general melee]
Arrr, ye scallywags!
You're gonna swab the poop deck!
[KIDS] (giggling)
[KOBORY] Those boys are
definitely lovers. (sigh...)
What?
You're one of my followers?
[MOTHER] I'm a huge fan! I've
seen all of your flame wars!
[SYLPHY] Ye Maaa...
Fen Zongggg...
sssshhhhhwwww!
Oh my, it looks like the
performance is already underway!
Yes, I can't wait for the bows.
[hmm] I shouldn't have
made you sneak around with me.
Forgive me, Triken.
Oh, no, I bow down before you,
Princess.
[LATIFAH] (hmmm?)
But only out of respect,
obviously.
[WRENCH] (panting)
Sorry it took so long!
[rushing water]
[JAW & SHIINA] (wwahhh!)
[WRENCH] Dad‐gum!
It should only take
a few minutes, right?
[WRENCH] Are you crazy?!
[JAW & SHIINA] (waahhh!)
[BOTH] (waahhhh!!)
[WRENCH] Whoa!
[laughing & mock fighting]
Get 'em, get 'em! (giggling)
[ON SPEAKER]
Oh, no that's not good!
Moffle and his friends have
just been captured!
But all of us can help!
[rumble]
Let's all cheer!
[ALL] (HUH?!)
[seals barking]
At last,
we've found ourselves a port.
Whoa,
what's going on over here?!
That big ugly guy's name
is Ironbeard.
Back in Maple Land,
he's known as the meanest
bully on the high seas.
[SEIYA] He must've gotten out
through the underground gate.
[MOFFLE] Probably.
[IRONBEARD] Arr, I was hopin'
to find meself some treasure
beyond the portal.
Ah, well, sellin' off
the wenches 'n brats
oughta bring in a pretty pile
o' gold doubloons at least.
[evil chuckle] I be the fearsome
pirate they call Ironbeard!
And I've come here to pillage
and pilfer the lot of ye!
So don't bother
puttin' up a fight!
[SEALS] (barking)
What's he doing, Mommy?
Uh‐oh, looks like the
bad guys are here!
Moff! Moff, moff, moff!
[ON SPEAKER] He says
"You won't get away with this!"
[hmm?] Ye might as well come
along quietly, mateys!
I might even let ye
join my crew!
[TIRAMY] Mii! Mii! Mii!
[EIKO ON SPEAKER] "No way,
we'd never work for you!"
A cryin' shame, that.
And I was gonna let ye have
yer fun with any wench ye like.
Resistance be futile!
[MOFFLE] MOFF! Tiramy!
[MACARON] Traitor‐ron!
Look, I know what I want, okay?!
[IRONBEARD]
Now, me hearties! Grab 'em!
[SEALS] (barking)
[canon shots]
[TIRAMY] Fire in the hole!
MOFF!
[KIDS] (wow!)
RON!
[EIKO ON SPEAKER]
I won't repeat that!
[GIRLS] Haa! Yah!
[SYLPHY] Zuo You Lou Xi Ao Bu...
[TRIKEN] Pr‐Princess Latifah,
you have to get out of here!
It's too dangerous! (wah!)
[SEALS] (barking)
Hyahhhh!
[bonk! bonk! bonk!]
[canon shot]
[IRONBEARD]
Quit yer wigglin' about!
[ALL] (gasp!)
(wahhh!)
[LATIFAH] Sir Kanie!
Um, this isn't good.
[ON SPEAKER] Oh, no,
Princess Latifah's been
kidnapped by the pirates!
[IRONBEARD] Avast!
It's time to celebrate!
[TIRAMY] Miiii!!
[SEALS] (barking)
[ON SPEAKER] This fella says
"Two more drinks over here,
little lady, and make
it snappy!"
Uh, okay!
Be right over!
[ON SPEAKER]
And this gentleman says
"Hey there, honey, whip us up
one strawberry and one lemon."
"On the double!"
Coming up! Hold on a minute!
I thought that was
all scripted,
so how is she translating
for the seals?
[IRONBEARD] (hearty laugh)
In all me years o' debauchery,
I never thought we'd manage to
make a hostage outta the
Princess of Maple Land!
Ahoy, what's with
all the dillydally?
Fetch me another drink,
ye wretched dogs!
[perky chrip]
[SYLPHY]
Zhuan Shen Ban Lan Chui.
[IRONBEARD] (uuhhh...)
[SYLPHY] (huh?)
J‐Just take the bottle,
little missy!
[LATIFAH] Right.
Here.
[ISUZU] (huh?)
They really went all out
with whatever this is!
Ron!
Now what?!
Our paws are tied.
We'll just have to sit tight and
see how everything plays out.
[bubbling] [alarm beeping]
[panting]
I'm alive...
[groan]
Hey, what's Jaw doing here?
[SHIINA] (uuhhh...)
[SEIYA] Chujo?!
You're eating people now?!
You monster!
Huh?
N‐n‐n‐no, wait!
You've g‐g‐got it all wrong!
M‐M‐Mr. Jaw was actually
t‐t‐t‐trying to save my l‐life,
so that's w‐w‐why I was‐
[JAW] (ughhh...)
M‐Mr. Ja‐ (WAAHHHH!!)
[GENJURO] Acting manager!
It's good to see you're okay!
[ah!] Glad you guys made it!
[sad sigh]
[mphff!] [bonk! bonk! bonk!]
[sneak, sneak, sneak]
Well, boys,
it seems the time has come!
[SEALS] (happy barking)
[ON SPEAKER]
They're very excited!
[deep breath...]
PEH!
[ALL] (AH!)
Ye three louts walk the plank.
[ALL] (HUH?!)
Bosun, do the honors.
Me?
[TIRAMY] MII!
[SYLPHY] Yo ho ho!
[ON SPEAKER] "Walk the plank!
Walk the plank!"
[SEALS] (rythmic barking)
[gasp]
[MACARON] Ow! Tiramy, how
could you do this to me, ron?!
Please don't let it
end like this! [waahhh...]
Listen!
It's okay, mii.
You know I would never push
my best pal into a pool of
squishy death, right?
[huh?!] Thanks, Tiramy.
So, you just follow my lead and
I promise I'll get you out of
this mess somehow, okay, mii?
Okay, got it.
What's the plan now? (ugh!)
[TIRMAY] Betrayal!
[waaaahhhh!]
[ungh...]
[ON SPEAKER] They're saying
"Look at him suffer!"
[SEALS] (happy barking)
Oh, no! Macaroooon!
[ON SPEAKER] "Walk the plank!
Walk the plank!"
[SEALS] (rythmic barking)
The best way to trick your enemy
is to trick your friends first.
Our comeback starts
right now, mii.
Moff, as if I'd fall for that.
Now, just stand right here
at the edge of the plank...
[evil chuckle]
[MOFFLE] (huh?!) Moff!
Mii!
Miiiiiiiiii!
[sprong!]
[BOTH] (oh!)
MOFF!
[MOFFLE] That's what I'll do.
[TIRAMY] Now, just stand at
the edge of the plank...
[MOFFLE] (mmm) Moff!
[uh...] Moooofffff!
[ungh...]
[SEALS] (happy barking)
[EIKO ON SPEAKER] They love it!
[SEALS] (rythmic barking)
Dude, what exactly were you
trying to do just now?
Okay, your turn!
They saved the best for last.
I think I have a plan,
if you'll just, um...
M‐mii...
[TIRAMY] (uuuhhh... um...)
[TIRAMY] (aaahhhh....)
Now HE'S walking?
Guess so.
Fire!
[canon shot]
[IRONBEARD] Hmm?
[LATIFAH] (gasp)
[SEALS] (panicked barking)
[IRONBEARD] (ah!)
[canon shot]
[MOLES] Yaaaah!
[ISUZU] (ah!)
Who's shooting the cannon?!
Kanie?!
[canon shots]
[IRONBEARD] On yer feet!
Yer comin' with me!
[ISUZU] (ah!)
[ISUZU] (gasp) The princess!
[LATIFAH] (nooooo!)
[gunshot]
[IRONBEARD] (argh!)
Are you okay there,
Miss Manager?
I'm all right, thank you.
[MOFFLE] Here we go!
It's time for a little payback!
Ronnn!
[SEALS] (ungh...)
Moff!
[KIDS] (laughing & cheering)
[ON SPEAKER] Look at that,
boys and girls, our friends
are here to rescue us!
So, I want you all to cheer
nice and loud for them, okay?
[loud cheering]
Uh‐oh,
whose side should I take now?
Arr, you'll pay for this!
[ISUZU] (ugh!)
[IORNBEARD] ARRR!
[ISUZU] Hyah!
[MOFFLE]
I knew this guy was tough!
[SEIYA] Avoid the
left side of the stage!
[canon shots]
That's where most of
the guests are!
Third cannon, get it together!
Second cannon, reload!
Ah, right away, Captain!
[grrr] [ah!]
[uh... um...]
Ready! Fire away!
[canon shot]
[waaahhhhh!]
[BIINO] (ahhh!)
[SEALS] (panting)
[BIINO] (waahh!)
[JAW] (WAAAHHHH!!)
[ALL] (HUH?!)
IT'S A SHARK!
[SEALS] (panicked barking)
[IRONBEARD]
St‐stay away from me!
Have mercy, I beg ye!
[ALL] (cowering & whining)
[PON SPEAKER]
Ironbeard and his gang of
pirates have surrendered!
I really love a happy ending!
Ew, strawberry syrup
is so sticky!
[cheering & laughing]
[hmph!] Yer a blitherin' fool
if ye think ye can treat the
great Ironbeard this way.
Sure I can. You just cost us
a fortune in damages.
And I'm gonna
make sure you pay.
Whatever it takes.
[hmph]
I'd like to see ye try. Yer a
That's enough out of you!
Unless you want double
your punishment!
[IRONBEARD] Ah, beggin'
yer pardon, sir.
[SEALS] (cowed barking)
Today was exciting, huh?
I had a lot of fun!
Can we come back soon, Mommy?
Of course!
Fine then, you guys'll
work here all summer long.
Without any compensation!
And I expect every guest
to be entertained.
I'll do no such thing,
ye bug‐brained scallyw‐
Stop your bellyaching.
[IRONBEARD] A‐aye, sir.
[SEALS] (whining)
Jaw...
[JAW] A‐at your service!
I'd like you to serve as their
team leader from now on.
Would you do that for me?
Are you sure you want ME, sir?!
[SEIYA] Yep! I need you to watch
out for them, onstage and off.
[gulp]
Right! I won't let you down!
M‐M‐Mr. Jaw, c‐congratulations!
I'M TRULY GRATEFUL!
Thank you so much!
It's an honor!
[SHIINA] (sobbing)
Sir Kanie...
I just wanted to apologize
to you for all that
happened here today.
It's entirely my fault that
everything got out of hand.
I'm terribly sorry.
Latifah...
[SEIYA]
What are you talking about?
[BOTH] (ah!)
I should say thank you!
[LATIFHA] (huh?)
Well, just take a look around!
A new side attraction...
[JAW] (crying)
New cast members...
A pirate ship!
And we basically got it
all for free!
It's kinda funny!
[laughing]
Oh...
All's well that ends well, mii!
You know what? Nobody has
anything to be sorry for!
[nervous laugh]
[ISUZU] But YOU do.
[TIRAMY] Wh‐Who, mii?
[LATIFAH] Lady Isuzu?
Please, try not to be
too harsh on him.
[ISUZU] As you wish, Princess.
You're lucky, Tiramy.
I'll let you say some
parting words before you die.
I just wanna say that I
have faith in all of you!
I know you guys would never do
something like this to one of
your own, right, mii?!
[MACARON] Ha!
That's a good one, buddy‐ron.
[MOFFLE] Yeah, if that's the
case, then it's a good thing
you're not one of us.
[TIRAMY] Mii!
[BOTH]
(HUH?!)
MMMIIII!!!
RROOONNNN!!!
MMOOOFFFF!!!
[TAKAYA] Well, well, well!
Never thought you'd end up
being acting manager.
Look, is there anything
I can do for you?
No, not really.
I just wanted to peek in
on you for a bit.
From what I understand,
your visitor count's
been looking a little more
optimistic since the
last time I saw you.
I think I get it.
[SEIYA] I really don't know
that I've done much of
anything yet.
[chuckle] Well, then, I suggest
you give it your best shot,
Mister Celebrity.
Tick‐tock!
All right,
let's do one last check!
[MACARON] Front!
Back!
Skirt!
Good! It's gonna be perfect!
[ISUZU & SEIYA] Time for
the attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU]
Today's feature is Blue Ocean.
It's useful for drawing in
customers during the summer.
[SEIYA] Better than anything
else does, I guess.
[ISUZU] But just like
what happened today,
it does connect to other worlds
from time to time.
We've already had to deal with
a kraken and a giant octopus.
[SEIYA] And it wasn't
all over the news?!
[ISUZU] Genjuro, the dolphin,
always feels responsible,
so he usually commits
ritual suicide.
[SEIYA] He USUALLY does?!