[EIKO]
Come meet the lovable mascot
characters from Maple Land,
the kingdom of dreams!
[EIKO]
Where fairy tales come to life!
[GAL A/GAL B]
(laughing)
[EIKO]
With so many great
attractions...
there's always something fun
for the whole family!
[BOY C] Yeah!
[GIRL B] (happy)
[GIRL C/GIRL D]
(happy jumping)
[EIKO]
The memories will
last a lifetime.
[GIRL E] Yum!(chomp)
[TODDLER A] (big bite)
[EIKO]
So plan your visit to
Amagi Brilliant Park today!
[TRIKEN]
So what do you think of it?
I wanted this promotional video
to be perfect
so I poured my blood sweat
and tears into it.
[SEIYA]
It's okay...
Not bad, but not good either.
Actually, the whole thing
is pretty bland.
[TRIKEN]
So you don't like it?
[SEIYA]
No, not at all...
It looks like you created
a visual representation of your
boring personality.
[TRIKEN]
(frown)
[SEIYA]
I see this happen a lot.
All the fundamentals are there,
but it still puts me to sleep.
[SEIYA]
To be totally frank,
the product is boring
because the person
who made it is boring.
[SEIYA]
You get it?
[TRIKEN]
And he wonders why
he has no friends.
[SEIYA] Did you say something?
[TRIKEN] Not at all!
[SEIYA]
Here's the thing, Triken,
I am way too busy to hold your
hand through all of this today.
[SEIYA]
Sento.
[ISUZU]
Yes?
[SEIYA]
You were listening, weren't you?
Tell Triken what he needs to do.
[ISUZU]
Well alright... but to be fair,
I don't know anything about
making videos either.
[SEIYA]
Yeah, but two heads
are better than one.
[ISUZU] Understood.
It might be smart to ask
the other workers
for their input too...
I'll look over the final
product when you're finished.
[TRIKEN]
Thank you for your assistance!
Please excuse me...
It's time to
hunch over and work!
[ISUZU]
PV... "Promotional video"
is that right?
Unfortunately,
as I told you before...
I don't know
the first thing about this.
I don't understand
what makes the video
so unsatisfactory.
But I do agree with Kanie
that something's not right.
[TRIKEN]
You think so too, do you?
[ISUZU]
I believe the logical first
step is to follow his advice
and gather input from the
rest of the cast.
[TRIKEN]
Input? What do you mean "input"?
[ISUZU]
Why don't we go see what
our star mascots think?
[MOFFLE]
Moff, this is no good.
[TRIKEN]
You didn't like it either.
[MOFFLE]
How do I describe it? Too plain?
This happens a lot.
All the fundamentals are there
but it still puts me to sleep.
It's like you've created
a visual representation of
your boring personality.
[TRIKEN]
He just said exactly what
Mr. Kanie said...
They're BOTH terrible.
[MOFFLE] You say something?
[TRIKEN] Not at all!
[MOFFLE]
If I had to pick out
the biggest problem,
I'd say it needs more action.
Like the fireworks
at the beginning...
explosions would be better.
[TRIKEN]
Did... you say explosions?
[MOFFLE]
All you need is a bit
of gasoline and then MOFF!
Get a shot of somebody running
past a bunch of explosions
and jumping straight
off a cliff!
Then at the end
you see the park logo
in front of the aftermath!
[TRIKEN]
Are you sure that's wise?
This park's supposed
to be family‐friendly.
[MOFFLE]
Don't think about too much.
Let's just try it
and see what happens!
[MOFFLE]
("moff" kicks)
[SWAT MAN A] (oof!)
[SWAT MAN B] (kicked)
[MOFFLE]
Moff.
[MACARON]
Ron!
[WANIPEE]
(nervous glances)
[TIRAMY]
Heheh...
[TRIKEN]
Is this any better?
[ISUZU]
Let's see...
I can't say for certain...
but I think so.
[TRIKEN]
Oh...! That's surprising.
[ISUZU]
For one... it's definitely
not boring now.
And the explosion scenes
are especially convincing.
You should proceed
along these lines.
[TRIKEN]
Yes Miss Isuzu... I'll see
what else we can add to it.
[MACARON]
Hmm...
This is okay I guess,
but doesn't tell
the audience anything
about the kind of music
I perform at the music
theater‐ron.
[TRIKEN]
Oh, I see.
If you ask me, the visuals
AND the soundtrack
could benefit from a more
"aggressive" tone.
[TRIKEN]
What do you mean by
"aggressive"?
[TIRAMY]
I'm thinkin' you gotta
crank up the libido‐mii!
[TRIKEN]
Uh... libido as in sex drive...?
[TIRAMY]
That's right. you know
what I'm talking about.
To put it in simple terms
I think we need to go lewder.
[TRIKEN]
Lewdness?!
Now THAT I understand!
[TIRAMY]
Swimsuits! Short skirts!
Low angles!
All you gotta do is
squeeze in as much fanservice
as you can legally
get away with‐mii!
But... we don't exactly
have enough room in the budget
to hire any models.
[TIRAMY]
No problem!
Lucky for you I've been building
my sexy secret stash for years!
[TRIKEN]
Secret stash?!
[TIRAMY]
(snicker)
Who needs to hire a model
when there's this many
gorgeous babes on the payroll?
[TRIKEN]
(amazed)
[TIRAMY]
It's about a terabyte's worth...
Perfectly organized, tagged,
and thumbnailed of course!
[TIRAMY]
I'll just go ahead and give you
complete access to the server
so you can do
whatever you want with 'em...
and I DO mean
whatever‐mii.(giggle)
[TRIKEN]
Ah! This is wonderful!
The Goddess Libra will
surely bless your generosity,
my friend!
[TRIKEN]
Ooh, right there...!
Ahhh that's good...
YEEEEEEEEES! (lewd laughter)
[MACARON]
(metal scream)
[CROWD]
(synchronized headbanging)
[MODEL A]
Ooh...
[MODEL B]
(sexy giggle)
[MODEL C]
(moan)
[TRIKEN]
How do you like that?!
I'd say it's a masterpiece!
[ISUZU]
Since I'm clearly
not the target audience...
I shouldn't complain...
It's not my place to argue.
Personally... I think
it's extremely revolting but...
Oh well... I guess that's
just how the world works.
[TRIKEN]
I appreciate your understanding,
Miss Isuzu.
[ISUZU]
You know...
a few of these outfits
look strangely familiar...
I get the feeling
I've seen them before...
But you hired models
for this project right?
[TRIKEN]
Oh yes...! Of course I did!
[ISUZU]
These thighs, for example.
They're bothering me.
[TRIKEN]
You and me both!
[ISUZU]
Fair enough...
We'll keep this part in.
[TRIKEN]
Thank you so much, Miss Isuzu!
Look, I'm hunched over
with gratitude‐
[ISUZU]
Anyway... It seems unfair
to cater exclusively
to the male guests.
[TRIKEN]
What do you propose we do?
[ISUZU]
Let's get some advice
from the girls next.
[MODEL A]
Ooh...
[MODEL B]
(sexy giggle)
[MODEL C]
(moan)
[MUSE]
This looks kinda familiar to me.
[TRIKEN]
No it doesn't.
[KOBORY]
It's just...
explosions and sexy
pictures of girls.
[SALAMA]
Yeah, I'm kinda grossed out now.
Let's see what the internet
thinks about this.
[TRIKEN]
Ok... how can I make it better?
[SYLPHY] Ohh noo I misfired!
[MUSE] Where do I start?
[SYLPHY] We're all out of ammo!
[KOBORY]
Uh, listen... This is...
just a... suggestion...
but right now there's
nothing at all in this video
that appeals to
a female audience.
[KOBORY] So um...
We need male nudity...!
[SYLPHY] Request evac ASAP!
As many hot naked guys
as possible!
[TRIKEN] Huh?
[KOBORY]
Girls want to see lots of
guy‐on‐guy action
and tiny speedos...!
Oh and plenty of close‐up shots
of their bulging muscles too!
[SALAMA]
I think that's just what
YOU want to see.
[TRIKEN]
Oh no, any suggestions
you girls can give
[TRIKEN] are more than welcome.
[SYLPHY] Ready for liftoff!
[TRIKEN] After all,
that's what I'm here for.
[SYLPHY] Searching for target...
Enemy target sighted
at one o'clock.
[MUSE]
Well, if you're asking
what we like,
I wouldn't mind
some shots of water.
[SYLPHY] Wind 0. Visibility...
[TRIKEN]
You just mean normal
water scenes, right?
[SYLPHY] Liftoff countdown...
[MUSE]
Yes! Looking at the water
is so relaxing.
[SYLPHY] Ready and...
I have lots of footage
of rivers and oceans
if you want me to
send them to you.
[SYLPHY]
Waaahhh the mission failed...!
[SALAMA] If that's the case,
‐Thank you for your sacrifice!
[SALAMA] I think I might have
a contribution to make too!
[TRIKEN]
Oh?
[SALAMA]
I'm pretty sure you'll like it.
[MUSE]
(snooze)
(shriek) Why do you have that?
Delete it right now!
(freaking out)
[SALAMA]
They're from that sleepover
at your place.
[MUSE]
(flustered, into surprised)
[SALAMA]
I just sent them to you, Triken.
Hopefully you'll be able to
use them for something good.
[TRIKEN]
Yes ma'am...! I assure you
they'll be VERY beneficial.
[MUSE]
No way! I won't
let you have them!
[MUSE]
(wailing)
(snooze)
[MODEL D]
Ooh...
[MODEL E]
(sexy giggle)
[MODEL F]
Yum...
[TRIKEN]
So what do you think of it?
[ISUZU]
I'm not... sure WHAT to think.
I can't believe these are
the models you selected.
[TRIKEN]
Well... actually
we were low on funding
after I DEFINITELY hired models
for the first one,
so I asked the gentlemen
from security to help us out.
[ISUZU]
You mean Okuro and the others?
[TRIKEN]
Yes, luckily some of the new
part‐timers were willing
to play along too.
[ISUZU]
Couldn't you have
enlisted someone else?
Surely they're not
the most attractive men
you could've asked.
[TRIKEN]
Oh? Is there anyone in
particular?
[ISUZU]
Well...
Nevermind.
[TRIKEN]
You were talking about
Mr. Kanie, weren't you?
[ISUZU]
Shut your mouth.
[TRIKEN]
I nailed it, didn't I?!
Nothing gets past old Triken!
Don't even bother trying to‐
[ISUZU]
I said shut it.
[TRIKEN]
Consider it shut.
[ISUZU]
Anyway... do we really need
footage of a river flowing
or Muse taking a nap?
[ISUZU]
Surprisingly,
Sylphy's contribution
is the most relevant.
[TRIKEN]
You're right, that's kind of an
unexpected twist, isn't it?
[ISUZU]
I think we need to ask for other
people's opinions now.
What about the
most important person?
Talk to her next.
[TRIKEN]
The most important person,
you say?
[LATIFAH]
Yes...? Did you need me?
A promotional video?
I'm sorry...
but I wouldn't know how to help
with something like that.
[TRIKEN]
Anything will be helpful...
Perhaps you could tell me
what sort of things
you'd like the video
to be about.
[LATIFAH]
Hmm...
Oh I know...!
This is the
perfect opportunity...!
Why don't you feature
the park employees
who work behind the scenes
so they can have a chance
to shine for a change?
[MOLE A]
(carrying)
[MOLE B]
[TARAMO]
A promo? Well I'll be!
Maybe this is what
you're looking for.
[TRIKEN]
I see...
[NICK]
You're making a video?
[TRIKEN]
That's right...! Do you think I
could get a shot of you cooking?
[NICK]
No thanks... too much effort.
[TRIKEN]
Excuse me, Mr. Wrench‐
[WRENCH]
Dammit all, can'tcha see
I'm busy?!
[OKURO]
Huh? You're filming again?
Yes. But this time
I want to focus on the
security force as a whole.
Perhaps I'll get some footage
of you working the gate
or training other employees,
things of that nature.
[OKURO]
Oh really? That sounds good.
[ASHE]
I'm sorry, I'm not sure how to
make accounting
look interesting on video...
So what should I do?
[TRIKEN]
That's alright, Miss Ashe,
it doesn't have to be your job;
it could be something you do
on your days off.
It just needs to represent
who you are as a person.
[ASHE]
Who I am? Well then...
[RUBRUM]
I might have something
interesting...
from back in my school days.
[TRIKEN]
Ah... and what is that?
[RUBRUM]
Footage of my club activities.
[DORNELL]
You need help with a promo?
[TRIKEN]
Right, I'm looking
for suggestions
from as many park employees
as possible.
I'd love to come up
with something unique
that makes a big impact.
[DORNELL]
Wouldn't you know it
I have just the thing.
It's something I made
with a group of
like‐minded individuals.
[JACK]
If you gimme some time...
I'll go on a wild west adventure
and film it for ya.
[GENJURO]
I think this noble endeavor
could greatly benefit
from the spirit of the samurai!
[IRONBEARD]
Aye lads, an' I'd wager
a fine pirate like meself'd
be a perfect addition.
[FUTURE]
What about a hard‐hitting drama
about saving the earth?
[TRIKEN]
Hello... Mr. Codain?
What do you think?
[TRIKEN]
Do you ever talk at all?
Ah! What's that?
Okay, today
I'm gonna demonstrate
the proper method
for slicing meat...
First you hold the knife
just like this and then...
I SAID BEAT IT!
[PRO WRESTLER/OKURO]
(lockup)
[OKURO]
(punched)(effort)
[PRO WRESTLER]
(punch)(splutter)
[GUY A]
That's awesome!
[DORNELL]
I feel so inspired now!
[GUY B]
Totally worth the trip!
[GUY C]
Look this way, guys,
you're on video!
[JACK]
Hyahhhh!
(kicked off)
[GENJURO]
(inhale) In my final hour...
my humble heart
is cleansed of all regret.
For I know I sacrifice my life
for the sake of
countless others.
(seppuku grunt)
[ISUZU]
I didn't understand that...
but I think it works.
[TRIKEN]
What?! THIS is what we want?
[ISUZU]
I'm curious about Ashe's part...
What on earth was she doing?
It's a competitive sport
known as extreme ironing...
Apparently you're supposed to
iron clothes in bizarre places.
Well, I suppose we all have
our hobbies, don't we?
[ISUZU]
I didn't really understand
the part with Dornell
visiting the dam either.
[TRIKEN]
I wasn't aware of it before,
but it turns out there's quite
a fan base for dams.
[ISUZU]
Well alright then...
Each part of the video does seem
special in its own way,
so it covers a wide range
of interests.
[TRIKEN]
Indeed... and I believe
we have enough footage
to work with at this point,
wouldn't you agree?
[ISUZU]
Oh I don't think
I'd say that yet...
The next step is to hear
the opinion of someone
who's closer to
a visitor's viewpoint.
[TRIKEN]
And where are we
going to get that?
[ISUZU]
Talk to those three girls
we hired recently.
[BIINO]
I'd say it needs more
blood and guts!
[TRIKEN]
Why blood and guts?!
[BIINO]
You know...! Everybody likes
to watch things
that creep them out, don't they?
So just throw in a bit
of violence and it'll be
a masterpiece.
Trust me on this one...
It's gonna be a big hit
with the visitors.
[TRIKEN]
Well... i‐if you're
sure about it...
[SHIINA]
I... I think the video
looks fonderwul!
N‐no wait I mean... W‐wonderful!
[TRIKEN]
Is that how you honestly feel?
[SHIINA]
W‐well... maybe...
you uh... (nervous)
Actually nevermind,
don't worry about it!
[TRIKEN]
Hmmm...
[EIKO]
Wow Triken...
I think you've done
a beautiful job with this.
[TRIKEN]
You think it's beautiful?
[EIKO]
Of course...! Although...
if you wouldn't mind me stating
my own personal opinion...
I just can't help
but feel that it's
lacking a certain emotional
quality in its current state.
[TRIKEN]
Emotional?
Do you have an example?
[EIKO]
You see... I happen to be quite
interested in horses.
They've been a hobby of mine
since I was a girl, actually.
[TRIKEN]
Huh.
[EIKO]
And not too long ago,
I was lucky enough
to have a chance to witness
a mother horse giving birth.
It was a horse that's been
very special to me
since I was in high school...
Her name's Kikuno Scepter,
isn't that sweet?
[TRIKEN]
That's an interesting name...
[EIKO]
The delivery was
extremely difficult...
but now she's a proud mother!
In all my life...
I've never been so moved!
[TRIKEN]
(extended amazement)
Finished!
[TRIKEN]
It's amazing!
[GAL A/GAL B]
(laughing)
[GIRL A]
(giggle)
[BOY B]
[MODEL A]
Ooh...
[MODEL B]
(sexy giggle)
[MODEL F]
Yum...
[MACARON]
(metal scream)
[OKURO/PRO WRESTLER]
(grunt)
[OKURO] (punched)
[PRO WRESTLER] (pain)
[MODEL C]
(moan)
[MOFFLE]
("moff" kick)
[SWAT MAN A]
(oof!)
[MOFFLE]
Moff.
[MACARON]
Ron!
[TIRAMY]
Heheh...
[GUY A]
That's awesome!
[DORNELL]
I feel so inspired now!
[GUY B]
Totally worth the trip!
[GUY C]
Look this way guys‐
[JACK]
Hyahhh!
[GENJURO]
(seppuku grunt)
[MODEL F]
Yum...
[MUSE]
(snooze)
[CROWD]
(synchronized headbanging)
First you hold the knife
just like this and then...
[WRENCH]
I SAID BEAT IT!
[JACK]
(kicked off)
[MODEL F]
Yum...
[WANIPEE]
(slo‐mo death)
[GUY D]
It's taking too long!
If this keeps up,
Kikuno won't make it!
[GUY E]
Let's pull it out!
[GUY D]
It's a tough angle,
but I think we're gonna have to!
[GUY D] Get ready!
[GUY E] Right!
[GUY D]
Hang in there, Kikuno!
[GUY E]
Kikuno, push!
[GUY D]
Come on out, we're almost there!
[GUY E]
She's standing up!
[GUY D/GUY E]
(heavy breathing,
into happy laughter)
[SEIYA]
What the hell did you DO?!
Ah yes, I knew I'd get a big
reaction from you, Mr. Kanie.
Sento...!
You were supposed to be
supervising this project!
What were you doing?!
[ISUZU]
I'm so moved!
What?!
[ISUZU]
It's a touching story...
of dreams coming true...
What's not to like about it?
[SEIYA]
Everything!
(cast complaining)
[MOFFLE]
Moff, not enough action.
[DORNELL]
Yeah and what happened
to the dam?
[MACARON]
Nah, the real problem
is the music selection‐ron.
[TARAMO]
I thought you were gonna
use our footage.
[TIRAMY]
Where's my collection of
sexy pictures‐mii?
[WANIPEE]
I don't understand why
nobody bothered asking ME
for an idea.
[SEIYA]
Quit complaining...!
We can't use that one.
[TRIKEN]
Actually Mr. Kanie,
I took it upon myself
to upload the other video
to the internet as well.
You what?!
And it's going viral.
No way!
[SEIYA/ISUZU]
Time for the
attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU]
Today's feature is Whip Antique.
[SEIYA]
Wait, this was the last episode.
And why does it say "no image"?
ISUZU
Don't worry about it.
Whip Antique.
Where fantasies come true.
Everybody loves Whip Antique.
Did you need to repeat that?
Come on down to Whip Antique.
[SEIYA]
I get it. This is some kind of
advertisement.
[ISUZU]
Remember, it's Whip Antique.
I'm not sure what kind of shop
it is, or what they sell.
[SEIYA]
Don't you think
that's important?!