♪
Kars: THE SPINES THAT THIS MASK
USES CAN PIERCE A HUMAN BRAIN.
HOWEVER, THEY DON'T YET
HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO PROBE OUR IMMORTAL BRAINS.
THE SOLUTION
IS FINDING MORE POWER.
Esidisi: OOH. WHAT'S THAT NOW?
Kars: THE MORTALS CALL IT
THE RED STONE OF AJA.
ITS POWER IS OF A PARTICULAR
INTEREST FOR OUR KIND.
THIS LITTLE STONE
CAN REFRACT LIGHT
AT LEAST A BILLION TIMES.
THE END RESULT IS LIGHT OF
INCREDIBLE PURITY AND STRENGTH.
THIS AMPLIFIED LIGHT
HOLDS POWER UNTOLD.
BUT THIS ONE WON'T DO.
THIS LITTLE RED PEBBLE
ISN'T LARGE ENOUGH.
WE NEED MORE CAPACITY
AND STRENGTH IN IT.
TO COMPLETE OUR MASK,
WE NEED A RED STONE
THAT IS LARGE
AND UTTERLY FLAWLESS.
WE NEED A SUPER AJA.
ONCE WE HAVE THAT,
WE WILL CONQUER THE SUN
AND THEN BECOME THE FINAL,
PERFECT STEP IN EVOLUTION.
Lisa Lisa:
THE MASKS WERE INVENTED
BY THE OLDEST PILLAR MAN
AMONG THEM,
AND HIS NAME IS KARS.
‐ Caesar: EH?
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
Lisa Lisa:
KARS, ESIDISI, AND WAMUU
CROSSED THE ATLANTIC
IN THEIR SEARCH
FOR A SUITABLE SUPER AJA.
THERE YOU ARE, SUZIE Q.
Suzie Q: SIGNORA, HERE.
JUST LIKE YOU WANTED.
Lisa Lisa: THANK YOU.
YOU SEE THIS?
WHAT I HAVE IN MY HAND HERE
IS A NATURAL,
PERFECTLY FLAWLESS STONE,
A SUPER AJA.
‐ JoJo: WOW.
‐ Caesar: WHOA.
JoJo: YOU'VE BEEN CARRYING
THE RED STONE OF AJA AROUND?
( both gasp )
Lisa Lisa: THE WARRIORS OF HAMON
WERE WIPED OUT
BY THE PILLAR MEN.
THIS STONE
NARROWLY AVOIDED BEING TAKEN,
AND NOW I HAVE BEEN GIVEN
THE HONOR TO BE ITS GUARDIAN.
( Caesar growls )
( JoJo thinking ) CAESAR,
I KNOW EXACTLY HOW YOU FEEL.
THE STONE MASKS NOT ONLY
KILLED OUR GRANDFATHERS,
BUT THEY TOOK THE LIVES
OF COUNTLESS OTHERS AS WELL,
AND NOW WE'VE MET
ITS CREATOR, KARS.
( aloud )
JUST BREAK IT.
YEAH, CRUSH THE DAMN THING.
SMASH IT TO PIECES,
AND THEY'LL CRY LIKE BABIES.
Lisa Lisa: NO, I CAN'T DO THAT.
JoJo: WHY? WHAT'S STOPPING YOU?
Lisa Lisa: LEGEND SAYS
THE PILLAR MEN CAN'T BE DEFEATED
UNLESS THE STONE IS SOMEHOW
A PART OF THE PROCESS.
JoJo: WHAT? THAT'S CRAZY.
WHY WOULD THAT BE?
Lisa Lisa: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I WILL PERFORM MY DUTY
AS GUARDIAN AS BEST I CAN.
JOJO, CAESAR,
I'M AFRAID IT'S NECESSARY
FOR A FINAL EXAMINATION.
Both: WHAT? A FINAL EXAM?
Lisa Lisa: CAESAR,
TAKE ON MESHINA, AND DEFEAT HIM.
JOJO, YOU HAVE
THE SAME ASSIGNMENT,
BUT WITH LOGGS.
ARE YOU TWO READY?
( both grunt )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Meshina: ARE YOU READY, CAESAR?
Caesar: I WAS BORN READY.
( both yell )
JoJo: IT'S ALMOST DAWN.
IT'S ALWAYS DARKEST THEN.
NOW, WHERE COULD I
EXPECT LOGGS TO BE HIDING?
STAY SHARP, JOSEPH. EYES OPEN.
YOU'VE GOT A SCORE
TO SETTLE WITH HIM.
HUH?
IS THAT INSTRUCTOR LOGGS?
( gasps ) HORRIBLE. UNNATURAL.
INSTRUCTOR LOGGS...
H‐HE'S DEAD!
♪
( gasps ) ESIDISI.
SO YOU CAME TO VENICE,
CAME HERE TO THIS ISLAND.
( Esidisi sighs )
( JoJo growls )
( Esidisi scoffs ) HMM.
TO THINK THAT THE WOMAN
GUARDING THE STONE
IS MERELY AN ISLAND OR TWO
OVER THAT WAY.
♪
JoJo: HIS LUNGS WERE PULLED OUT.
LUNGS ARE VITAL FOR HAMON USERS.
IT HAD TO HAVE BEEN A KICK
OF INCREDIBLE POWER.
THE TYRANT LOGGS.
YOU YELLED AT ME
FOR THREE WEEKS.
YOU WERE RELENTLESS
WITH YOUR INSTRUCTIONS.
TO BE HONEST, I HATED YOU.
I WAS SURE THAT THIS
WOULD BE MY CHANCE
TO GET YOU BACK
FOR EVERYTHING YOU DID TO ME.
YOU'LL HAVE TO WATCH ME FROM
WHERE YOU ARE NOW, INSTRUCTOR.
SEE WHAT I'VE LEARNED FROM YOU.
♪
HEY, ESIDISI,
I KNOW IT'S SIX DAYS EARLY,
BUT I'LL TAKE IT NOW.
THAT ANTIDOTE IN YOUR NOSE RING
IS MINE!
Esidisi: HMM.
OUT OF MY WAY, BOY.
I DON'T HAVE THE TIME
TO DEAL WITH YOU.
JoJo: YOU DON'T HAVE THE TIME?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU HAVE A LOT MORE TIME
THAN I DO.
( both grunt )
Esidisi: THAT WAS PRETTY SHARP.
YOU MAY HAVE
A LITTLE MORE TO OFFER.
BUT WHEN SOMEONE LOOKS AT ME
WITH AN OBVIOUS CHALLENGE
LIKE THAT ONE,
THEY ARE ASKING FOR THEIR DEATH.
I'LL TELL YOU THIS
ONE MORE TIME.
BACK AWAY.
YOU KNOW THAT WITH
ONE TOUCH OF MY HAND,
YOU'LL SOON BE MISSING
HALF OF YOUR BODY.
JoJo: JUST TRY TO MOVE ME.
Esidisi: OOH. WHAT'S THIS NOW?
JoJo: OH, LOOK. I'M STILL HERE.
I ONLY MOVE
FOR IMPORTANT THINGS,
LIKE DOG POO IN MY PATH.
( Esidisi gasps )
USING HIS HAMON,
HE'S ABLE TO BREAK
RIGHT THROUGH
THE FLESH OF MY HAND.
HE'S LEARNED
A GREAT DEAL OF CONTROL
IN A VERY SHORT PERIOD OF TIME.
‐ HOWEVER...
‐ ( JoJo gasping )
Esidisi: YOU'VE DEVELOPED
NEW SKILLS.
I HAVE TO SAY
I'M RATHER SURPRISED.
( JoJo winces )
Esidisi: BUT YOU'RE STILL
FAR FROM READY
TO FIGHT SOMEONE LIKE ME!
I'VE MET AND DEVOURED
COUNTLESS HAMON USERS LIKE YOU
THOUSANDS OF YEARS AGO!
( JoJo screams )
Esidisi: IF I TWIST
YOUR FINGER COMPLETELY OFF,
YOU'LL NEVER USE IT
FOR HAMON EVER AGAIN.
( JoJo screams )
Esidisi: LIKE THIS!
HMM? EH?
JoJo: OH, YOU FINALLY NOTICED?
YOUR ARM IS WRAPPED UP
IN A LOOP OF FINE SILK THREAD.
IT'S SOAKED IN VEGETABLE OIL,
SO IT REALLY CONDUCTS HAMON
QUITE WELL.
I ADMIT I WAS AIMING
FOR YOUR NECK,
BUT YOU DIDN'T
GIVE ME THE CHANCE.
Esidisi: HOW COULD A MORTAL
HAVE DONE THIS TO ME?
( gasping )
BUT‐‐BUT THAT'S...
JoJo: ACTUALLY A LITTLE MORBID
FOR MY TASTE,
BUT STILL, FIRST BLOOD
GOES TO ME AND MY INSTRUCTOR!
( Esidisi screams )
2,500 YEARS AGO IN CHINA,
A MAN WROTE "THE ART OF WAR."
HE SAID THIS‐‐
"VICTORY IS DECIDED
BEFORE THE BATTLE IS FOUGHT."
THAT MEANS IF YOU PLAN TO WIN,
YOU NEED TO LAY OUT STRATEGIES
WHILE YOUR OPPONENT IS UNAWARE.
IT'S TRUE THAT I
SKIPPED SCHOOL A LOT,
BUT GRANNY ERINA MADE DARN SURE
I STUDIED MY HISTORY.
SO WHILE YOU MAY HAVE
A LOT OF YEARS UNDER YOUR BELT,
YOU DIDN'T LEAVE ANY ROOM
IN YOUR HEAD FOR STRATEGY.
( laughs )
TAKE THIS!
( Esidisi growls )
HOW DARE YOU?
JoJo: AWW. ARE YOU ANGRY?
ARE YOU UPSET THAT I
DISINTEGRATED YOUR WIDDLE ARM?
WELL, THEN, GET UPSET!
I'M FAR MORE FURIOUS THAN YOU.
BECAUSE OF THAT LITTLE RING YOU
SAW FIT TO PUT INSIDE MY NECK,
I HAVEN'T SLEPT RIGHT FOR WEEKS.
( Esidisi blubbering )
JoJo: HUH?
Esidisi: I JUST CAN'T TAKE IT!
( sobbing )
I JUST CAN'T TAKE IT!
JoJo: WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
HE'S BAWLING HIS EYES OUT,
AND I THOUGHT
HE'D GO ON A BLOODY RAMPAGE.
THIS IS MORE THAN WEIRD.
THIS IS EMBARRASSING.
HE'S THROWING A TANTRUM
LIKE SOME THREE‐YEAR‐OLD.
( Esidisi wailing )
MY POOR ARM!
JoJo: EHH.
SOME THINGS ARE CREEPIER
THAN MINDLESS ANGER.
I SHOULD FINISH HIM OFF QUICKLY.
( Esidisi crying )
‐ ( crying stops )
‐ JoJo: EH?
( Esidisi sighs )
♪
( sighs ) I FEEL BETTER NOW.
SOMETIMES MY EMOTIONS
OVERWHELM ME,
AND WHEN I'M ABOUT TO LOSE IT,
I TRY TO CALM MYSELF DOWN
BY VENTING WITH A CRYING JAG.
( JoJo gasps )
Esidisi: EARLIER YOU REFERRED
TO SUN TZU, DIDN'T YOU?
I KNEW HIM PERSONALLY.
LONG AGO,
I JOURNEYED TO CHINA TO STUDY.
TO FIGHT IS TO DELUDE.
ALL WAR IS DECEPTION.
ONE TRIES TO MAKE
THEIR ENEMIES ANGRY
IN ORDER TO LURE THEM
INTO COMMITTING COSTLY MISTAKES.
THAT IS PRECISELY WHAT YOU'RE
PLANNING ON. AM I RIGHT?
WELL, IT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
BUT I MUST SAY, JOJO,
I REALLY AM SHOCKED
AT YOUR IMPROVEMENT.
I ADMIRE YOUR HAMON ABILITY.
I'VE BEEN LONGING
FOR A WORTHY OPPONENT.
JoJo: WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Esidisi: HUH.
WELL, IT IS A BIT THIN
AT THE MOMENT,
BUT IT'LL GROW THICKER
WITH THE PASSAGE OF TIME.
( JoJo gasps )
HE'S TOO MUCH.
JUST A MINUTE AGO,
HE WAS CRYING.
Esidisi: OH, JOJO,
DID I JUST FRIGHTEN YOU THERE?
COME ON. ADMIT IT.
YOU'RE FRIGHTENED A LOT,
AREN'T YOU?
( JoJo gasps )
I CAN'T READ HIM.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN ABLE
TO READ MY OPPONENTS
AND THEN USE THEIR OWN FEELINGS
AGAINST THEM,
BUT THIS GUY'S PERSONALITY
IS BEYOND ME.
AM I THE ONE
WHO'S BEING READ HERE?
W‐WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO LOGGS'S BODY?
GAH!
THAT BURNS.
HIS BODY, IT'S BOILING.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Esidisi: AN ANIMAL'S
CORE TEMPERATURE WILL INCREASE
WHEN IT'S FIGHTING DISEASE
OR GREATLY EXERTING ITSELF.
I CAN RAISE MY BLOOD
UP TO 500 DEGREES
AND THEN SHOOT IT OUT AT WILL.
AT THE SAME TIME
I TOOK OFF HIS ARM,
I ALSO SENT IN SOME
OF MY BOILING BLOOD TO SHOW YOU.
WITH HIS DIVINE SANDSTORM,
WAMUU CAN CONTROL THE WIND.
MY DOMAIN IS THAT OF HEAT.
I CONTROL THE INFERNO.
JoJo: I'LL GRANT THAT YOUR POWER
TO DESTROY A DEFENSELESS
DEAD BODY IS AMAZING,
BUT I CAN ALSO SEE
THAT THE REASON YOU DID IT
WAS TO TRY AND SCARE ME.
NOW TRY A CLACKER VOLLEY!
MY HAMON ISN'T
LIKE IT WAS A MONTH AGO.
( JoJo gasps )
Esidisi:
I REALLY DID FRIGHTEN YOU.
YOU SEE, JOJO,
YOUR UNCONTROLLED EMOTIONS
CAUSED YOU TO ATTACK ME
RECKLESSLY AND TOO SOON.
MY VEINS WILL INJECT
BOILING BLOOD INTO YOUR SKULL
AND THEN TURN YOUR BRAIN
INTO A NICE RED STEW.
THIS IS THE REASON THAT I AM
CALLED THE BURNING KING.
( JoJo gasps )
( screams )
( both gasp )
Lisa Lisa: JOJO.
♪
Meshina: CAESAR, TAKE THIS!
Caesar: BUBBLE LAUNCHER!
( Meshina yells )
CAESAR, STOP. HOLD YOUR ATTACK.
IF WE CONTINUE THIS CONTEST,
ONE OR BOTH OF US WILL DIE.
AND MUCH AS MY EGO DOESN'T WANT
TO ADMIT IT, I'D BE THE LOSER.
FOR NEARLY
10 YEARS MORE THAN YOU,
I HAVE BEEN IN PREPARATION HERE,
BUT TODAY YOUR HAMON ATTACK
WAS SO FOCUSED
YOU WERE ABLE TO BURN
THE HAIR OFF OF MY ARM.
WHAT ELSE CAN I DO
AFTER BEING SHAMED LIKE THIS?
YOU HAVE PASSED YOUR FINAL EXAM
WITH FLYING COLORS.
( Caesar grunts )
♪
Meshina: YOU SHOULD FEEL
A SENSE OF PRIDE FOR THIS.
OR ARE YOU MORE INTERESTED IN
HOW YOUR GOOD‐FOR‐NOTHING FRIEND
IS DOING IN HIS EXAM, CAESAR?
Caesar: THE ONLY REASON I HAD
THE POWER I DID IN THIS TRAINING
IS THAT I WANTED
TO MATCH JOJO'S TALENTS.
IN THE END,
WE'RE BOTH GOING TO SURVIVE
THE TRIALS
BEING PRESENTED TO US.
I CAN'T DENY IT.
JOJO SEEMS LAZY AND IMPUDENT,
BUT DEEP DOWN,
HE'S WORTH HAVING AS A FRIEND.
Meshina: HEH. YOU'RE NOT SO GOOD
AT MAKING FRIENDS
FOR YOURSELF, ARE YOU?
BUT WHEN YOU DO,
IT'S TRUE LOVE, ISN'T IT?
Caesar: WHA?! LOOK THERE!
ESIDISI!
Esidisi: HUMPH.
AND THERE'S ANOTHER
OF THOSE CLEVER DODGES OF YOURS.
JoJo: ALL RIGHT.
THE MASK GAVE ME
SOME PROTECTION
THAT TIME, BUT...
( screams )
HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT,
HOT, HOT. ( groans )
AH, DAMN HIM AND HIS BLOOD.
( growls )
MAN, OH, MAN, I FINALLY HAVE
THE CHANCE FOR THESE SEXY LIPS
TO COME OUT
FROM UNDER THAT ROTTEN MASK,
AND THE FIRST THING YOU DO,
YOU BASTARD, IS BURN 'EM OFF.
Esidisi: JOJO. HMM. LET'S SEE.
ON THE SURFACE,
YOU MAKE WITTY BANTER,
BUT INSIDE YOUR HEAD,
YOU'RE MAKING ALL SORTS
OF PLANS, AREN'T YOU?
( JoJo sputters )
Esidisi: OOH,
YOU WENT PALE, JOJO.
DID I HIT THE MARK?
WAS I ANYWHERE CLOSE
TO THE BULL'S‐EYE?!
( JoJo gasps )
HEH. MY NEXT PLAN.
RIGHT. YES.
I'LL USE THE STRING.
I'LL ACT LIKE I'M DODGING
TO GET AWAY FROM HIM,
BUT ALL THE TIME,
I'LL BE RUNNING A STRING
ALONG THESE SPIKES
WITH EACH MOVE I MAKE.
I CAN'T LET HIM CATCH ON.
ONCE HE STEPS INSIDE THE STRING,
I'LL WRAP HIM UP IN IT, THEN USE
MY HAMON TO FINISH HIM OFF.
( Esidisi scoffs, chuckling )
( JoJo gasps )
THAT LAUGH MEANS TROUBLE.
COULD‐‐COULD HE BE READING
MY PLAN, MY INTENTIONS?
NO, IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
( gasps )
( Esidisi chuckling )
( moans )
( chuckles )
‐ ( yells )
‐ JoJo: WHOA!
Esidisi: HERE IS
THE BURNING KING'S PRISON!
♪
HOW LONG CAN YOU POSSIBLY
KEEP AVOIDING MY ATTACKS, JOJO?
‐ JoJo: HUMPH.
‐ Esidisi: HUH?
JoJo: SO I GUESS
YOU FINALLY NOTICED.
NOW, WHAT POSSIBLE REASON
WOULD MY HAT BE SHRINKING?
YOU APPEAR TO BE CAUGHT
IN MY WEB.
MY HAT IS MADE OF 100% WOOL.
IT CONDUCTS HAMON VERY WELL.
Esidisi: AND?
JoJo: YOU'RE SMILING AGAIN.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING ABOUT THIS TIME?
Esidisi: THE NEXT WORDS
FROM YOUR MOUTH ARE,
"I'M GOING TO KNOCK THAT SMIRK
RIGHT OFF OF YOUR FACE." WATCH.
JoJo: I'M GOING TO KNOCK
THAT SMIRK RIGHT OFF YOUR FACE.
( gasps )
WHAT A SECOND.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
THAT'S MY TRICK.
Esidisi: YOU SAID YOU HAD A WEB?
LOOK AROUND.
I AM THE ONE WITH THE WEB.
I KNEW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU HAD IN MIND
WITH YOUR LITTLE PLAN
EVEN BEFORE YOU DID.
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( Esidisi chuckles )
SO, JOJO, WHAT WAS THAT PHRASE
YOU SAID EARLIER?
SOMETHING LIKE,
"VICTORY IS DECIDED
BEFORE THE BATTLE IS FOUGHT."
WAS THAT WHAT IT WAS?
IT'S TRUE, TRUE,
VERY TRUE, VERY TRUE, VERY TRUE!
HOW INCREDIBLY TRUE
WERE THE WORDS YOU SPOKE.
BUT MY PLANS
WERE THE ONES TO GO DEEPER.
MY PLANS WERE THE ONES
TO DECIDE VICTORY!
IT LOOKS LIKE MY VEINS
HAVE CREATED
SOME LITTLE HOLES ON YOUR BODY.
SO NOW I'LL FILL
EVERY ONE OF THEM
WITH A GENEROUS PORTION
OF MY BOILING, BURNING BLOOD.
YOU'LL LOOK LIKE A LOVELY
BIRTHDAY CAKE COVERED IN CANDLES
FLICKERING WITH
THEIR MERRY LITTLE RED FLAMES.
Caesar: HE'S ON A KNIFE'S EDGE.
HE'S NOT GOING TO MAKE IT.
Meshina: CAESAR!
JUDGING FROM WHAT I CAN SEE,
WE HAVE TO ASSUME
THAT LOGGS HAS BEEN KILLED.
IF JOJO IS
NOT THE ONE TO SURVIVE,
WE WILL BE THE ONES
ESIDISI WILL COME AFTER NEXT.
JOJO IS TOO FAR AWAY FOR US
TO BE ABLE TO HELP HIM NOW.
I KNOW IT'S PAINFUL,
BUT RIGHT NOW WE HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT PROTECTING LISA LISA
AND THE RED STONE,
SO COME.
LET'S MAKE OUR PREPARATIONS.
JOJO.
♪
Esidisi: LET ME
HEAR YOUR SCREAMS
AS YOU TWITCH AND WRITHE
IN DESPAIR AND AGONY,
KNOWING THAT YOU
LOST TODAY, JOJO.
( sizzling )
♪
‐ ( JoJo chuckles )
‐ ( Esidisi gasps )
( JoJo laughing )
Esidisi: ARE YOU REALLY LAUGHING
AS I'M ABOUT TO DEAL YOU
AN EXCRUCIATING DEATH?
HAVE YOU BEEN DRIVEN
COMPLETELY INSANE BY THE FEAR?
JoJo: WELL, LET'S SEE HERE.
YOU'LL NOTICE MY ARMS ARE FOLDED
AND MY EYES ARE CLOSED,
SO THIS LAUGH WOULD BE
ONE OF VICTORY, ESIDISI.
YOU'RE THE LOSER HERE TODAY,
BECAUSE FOR
THE LAST 2,000 YEARS,
YOU HAVE BEEN
ASLEEP AT THE WHEEL.
Esidisi: I LOST?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?!
JoJo: OH, REALLY?
YOU DON'T GET IT?
YOU CAN'T READ ME AS CLEARLY
AS YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD?
LET ME HELP YOU UNDERSTAND
JUST HOW BADLY
YOU'VE UNDERESTIMATED ME.
YOU SAID THAT YOUR PLANS
WENT DEEP.
WELL, THEY DIDN'T GO
NEARLY AS DEEP AS MINE.
( Esidisi growls )
JoJo: WHILE YOU WERE SNOOZING
FOR THE PAST 2,000 YEARS,
HUMANS HAVE PROGRESSED.
DURING THE 18th
AND 19th CENTURIES,
LEGERDEMAIN,
OR SLEIGHT OF HAND,
BECAME A VERY POPULAR
FORM OF ENTERTAINMENT.
I'M A REALLY BIG FAN
OF IT MYSELF.
ILLUSION IS MY THING!
Esidisi: BUT I CUT
ALL THOSE STRINGS.
I CUT THEM! IT CAN'T BE!
JoJo: I'D SAY
THE ROPE MAGIC WORKED.
I LAID MY TRAP CAREFULLY, SO
THAT EVEN IF THE STRING WAS CUT,
IT WOULD STILL FUNCTION.
A SIMPLE TRICK.
( Esidisi screams )
JoJo: WHAT YOU'RE
GOING TO SAY NEXT IS,
"MY VEINS WILL MOVE FASTER
THAN YOUR PATHETIC HAMON
CAN POSSIBLY GO." NOW.
Esidisi: MY VEINS
WILL MOVE FASTER
THAN YOUR PATHETIC HAMON
COULD POSSIBLY GO!
( JoJo breathes deeply )
NOW FEEL THE BEAT
OF MY HAMON OVERDRIVE!
( Esidisi screaming )
( squelch )
I CAN'T. I CAN'T.
YOU'RE ONLY A HUMAN.
I AM THE EVOLVED ONE,
THE HIGHEST LIFE‐FORM!
I WILL NOT BE BEATEN!
KNOW THAT YOU'VE
PUSHED ME TOO FAR!
( roars )
( screaming )
JoJo: ESIDISI'S BODY IS SHOOTING
SOME KIND OF STRANGE ENERGY.
THAT MUST COME
FROM LIVING FOR MILLENNIA.
DIE ALREADY.
DIE WITH THE POWER OF LIFE
YOU STOLE
FROM THOUSANDS
OF INNOCENT HUMAN BEINGS.
( Esidisi screaming )
JoJo: MY INSTRUCTOR,
I THANK YOU FOR TORTURING ME.
MILLE GRAZIE TO YOU, LOGGS.
( Esidisi screams )
( nose ring clatters )
HMM. WHEN WE DEFEATED
SANTVIENTO IN THE WELL,
HIS ENTIRE BODY
TURNED INTO STONE,
BUT EVEN ESIDISI'S BONES
WERE COMPLETELY DESTROYED.
WHY IS HE SO DIFFERENT?
WELL, MAYBE IT'S
BECAUSE MY HAMON
IS SO MUCH STRONGER
THAN IT WAS BEFORE.
WELL, HE'S DEAD NOW,
AND I HAVE ONE OF THE ANTIDOTES
I'VE BEEN CHASING DOWN.
UGH.
( sighs )
OH, MAN,
THIS REMINDS ME OF SNOT.
HOPEFULLY IT'S JUST BECAUSE
IT'S DRIPPING FROM A RING
THAT CAME OUT OF HIS NOSE.
BUT I NEED TO KNOCK IT BACK.
( grunting )
YES. I DO THINK IT WORKED.
THE RING AROUND MY WINDPIPE
IS GONE,
AND I CAN BREATHE FREE AGAIN.
SO THEN, I'LL GO SEE
LISA LISA AND CAESAR.
I THINK MAYBE I WAS USING
MY HEAD TOO MUCH IN THAT FIGHT.
( groans ) MY SHOULDERS
ARE REALLY KINDA STIFF.
( JoJo humming a tune )
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Suzie Q: I THINK
THE WHITE ONE IS PRETTY.
Caesar: WE'LL WAIT FOR THAT
UNTIL WE CROSS.
Suzie Q: BUT I REALLY LIKE
THE LOVELY DESIGN ON THIS ONE.
Meshina: I'LL ERADICATE
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
Suzie Q: WHICH DO I CHOOSE?
JoJo: DAMN IT ALL.
I JUST CAN'T HIT HER.