( thunder rumbling )
JoJo: YOU'RE A POISONER,
DIO BRANDO.
I HAVE ALL THE PROOF I REQUIRE
AND THEN SOME.
( Dio gasps )
( thunder crashes )
HE'S FOUND HIS PROOF. SO BE IT.
THIS MOMENT'S BEEN
A LONG TIME COMING, JOJO.
NOW I FINISH WHAT I STARTED.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
JoJo: I TRACKED DOWN
THE ANTIDOTE.
FATHER TOOK IT MOMENTS AGO.
DIO, THIS PAINS ME GREATLY.
FOR YEARS, YOU WERE MY BROTHER,
AND NOW I HAVE NO RECOURSE
BUT TO TURN YOU IN.
I'M SORRY, REALLY.
I'M SURE YOU DON'T BELIEVE
A WORD OF IT,
BUT I'M TELLING YOU THE TRUTH.
Dio: EVEN NOW,
YOU SHOW COMPASSION.
JOJO, I'VE BEEN A DEVIL,
BUT GRANT ME THIS ONE WISH.
ALLOW ME TO DO THE RIGHT THING
FOR ONCE IN MY LIFE
AND TURN MYSELF IN.
( JoJo gasps )
WHAT'S THIS?
I THOUGHT ONCE I CONFRONTED HIM,
HE'D FIGHT ME TOOTH AND NAIL
LIKE A CORNERED BEAST.
Dio: JOJO.
YOU SHOULD BE DEAD
IN A GUTTER RIGHT NOW.
I MUST DISTRACT HIM LONG ENOUGH
FOR THE KNIFE AND MASK
TO FIND THEIR MARK.
MY WICKED DEEDS GNAW AT ME.
THE POVERTY I KNEW AS A CHILD
ATE AWAY AT MY MORAL COMPASS
UNTIL GREED
WAS ALL THAT REMAINED.
I'M THE LOWEST OF THE LOW.
YOUR FATHER TOOK ME IN
OFF THE STREET,
AND I REPAID HIS KINDNESS
WITH POISON.
THE ONLY REASON I CAME BACK
WAS TO SURRENDER MYSELF.
IF I'D WANTED TO FLEE,
YOU NEVER WOULD HAVE
LAID EYES ON ME AGAIN.
JoJo: I SEE YOUR POINT.
Dio: PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO MAKE AMENDS.
JoJo: DIO.
Man: LOOK ALIVE, MASTER JOESTAR.
HE'S TRYING TO LURE YOU IN,
LIKE AS NOT.
RIGHT ABOUT NOW, YOU'RE PROBABLY
WONDERING WHO I AM.
ALLOW ME TO ELUCIDATE YA.
THE NAME IS
ROBERT E. O. SPEEDWAGON.
I HAD A HUNCH JONATHAN'S RUN
OF TROUBLE MIGHT NOT BE DONE,
SO I FOLLOWED HIM BACK HOME.
I LIKE YOU, JONATHAN,
SO I'M GONNA OFFER UP
THIS LITTLE TIDBIT PRO BONO.
LIVING IN THE GUTTER, YOU LEARN
TO SPOT LOWLIFES PRETTY QUICK
IF YOU WANT TO SEE TOMORROW.
I'VE TRAINED MY NOSE TO SORT OUT
THE BAD ONES FROM THE GOOD
JUST FROM A SNIFF.
THIS FELLA REEKS
OF BRIMSTONE AND BLOOD
WORSE THAN ANYONE
I'VE EVER LAID EYES ON!
HE IS PURE EVIL
RIGHT DOWN TO HIS VERY BONES!
IS HE A VICTIM OF CIRCUMSTANCE,
YOU'RE WONDERING?
NOT ON YOUR LIFE!
HE'S BEEN EVIL
SINCE HE DREW HIS FIRST BREATH.
( thunder crashes )
BUT DON'T YOU FRET,
'CAUSE I BROUGHT YOU A FRIEND.
REMEMBER HIM?
( Dio gasps )
JoJo: THIS MAN CONFESSED
TO SELLING YOU THE POISON
YOU USED ON FATHER.
( Dio sputters )
George: I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
YOU BREAK MY HEART.
WHY, DIO?
FROM THE DAY YOU ARRIVED,
I HAVE LOVED YOU AS THOUGH
YOU WERE MY OWN SON.
( coughs )
JoJo: FATHER, YOU'RE TOO WEAK
TO BE DOWN HERE.
George: YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'LL RETURN TO MY CHAMBER.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE
MY BOY IN CHAINS.
DO WHAT YOU MUST, JOJO.
JoJo: I WILL.
Dio: IS THIS HOW IT ALL ENDS?
Apothecary: HE WON'T SEE
THE INSIDE OF A CELL THIS NIGHT.
I READ HIS FACE AND THE TRIO
OF MOLES ON HIS EAR.
THE DEVIL SMILES ON HIM
AND GRANTS HIM LUCK.
( George grunts )
Dio: JOJO, I WANT YOU TO BE
THE ONE TO PUT THE CUFFS ON ME.
PLEASE, BROTHER.
JoJo: ALL RIGHT.
( chain rattles )
Speedwagon: BE CAREFUL.
HE'S A CRAFTY ONE.
Dio: JOJO, IT WAS HUBRIS THAT
LED ME TO THIS IGNOMINIOUS END.
THIS FALL FROM GRACE
HAS TAUGHT ME WELL.
HOWEVER ONE MAY SCHEME
AND DISSEMBLE,
MY DOWNFALL THIS NIGHT
IS PART OF THE HUMAN CONDITION,
A CONDITION I NOW FORSAKE.
JoJo: WAIT. FORSAKE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Dio: YOU SEE, I AM
ABOUT TO BECOME SO MUCH MORE!
HELP ME SHED THIS MORTAL SKIN.
JoJo: MOTHER'S MASK. BUT HOW?
Speedwagon: WATCH OUT.
Inspector: FIRE AT WILL, MEN.
Dio: JOJO,
YOUR BLOOD IS THE KEY!
( JoJo gasps )
( chain rattles )
( all gasp )
Speedwagon: OH, MY GOD.
George: FATHER!
( Dio laughing )
( laughing )
Inspector: SHOOT THAT MANIAC!
( thunder rumbles )
George: JOJO.
( JoJo gasps ) FATHER.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I SHOULD HAVE BLOCKED HIS KNIFE.
THE MASK.
WHEN I SAW IT, I FROZE UP,
AND YOU PAID THE PRICE.
( George grunts )
TAKE THIS RING.
IT WAS YOUR MOTHER'S, JOJO.
JoJo: FATHER.
Speedwagon: DAMN IT.
AIN'T A DOCTOR ON EARTH
WHO CAN FIX THAT.
HOW'D THAT DEVIL
GET THE DROP ON US?
Inspector: IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
IF ONLY I HADN'T LISTENED
TO YOU, SIR JOESTAR.
IF I HAD RUN HIS FATHER
OUT OF TOWN YEARS AGO
LIKE I'D A MIND TO,
NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE TAKEN PLACE.
Speedwagon: HOLD ON.
WHOSE FATHER?
Inspector: BACK WHEN I
FIRST JOINED THE FORCE,
THERE WAS A NE'ER‐DO‐WELL
WHO TRIED TO PAWN THAT VERY RING
YOU NOW SEE
ON JOESTAR'S FINGER.
THE SUSPECT WAS DIO'S
BIRTH FATHER, DARIO BRANDO.
George: IT'S MINE.
OF THAT, THERE'S NO DOUBT.
MY LATE WIFE AND I HAD THEM
MADE TO CELEBRATE OUR BETROTHAL.
Inspector: A LOCAL CUTPURSE
BY THE NAME OF DARIO BRANDO
‐ WAS TRYING TO SELL IT.
‐ George: HMM?
CAN IT BE?
Inspector: SIR JOESTAR THOUGHT
HE OWED HIS LIFE TO DARIO,
BUT HE WAS SADLY MISTAKEN.
DARIO HADN'T SCRAMBLED DOWN
TO THE MANGLED CARRIAGE
THAT FATEFUL NIGHT
TO LOOK FOR SURVIVORS,
BUT TO ROOT
FOR ILL‐GOTTEN RICHES.
Dario: HUH? YOU STAY BACK.
George: THIS MAN,
WHAT HAS HE SAID, INSPECTOR?
DID HE EVER TELL YOU
THAT I GAVE HIM THE RING?
Inspector: AYE.
HE SWORE UP AND DOWN.
YOU FILTHY LIAR.
George: HE SWORE
WITH GOOD REASON.
I GAVE HIM THE RING,
JUST AS HE TOLD YOU.
Inspector: YOU HAVE
GOT TO BE KIDDING!
Dario: EH?
George: HE IS INNOCENT.
LET HIM GO AT ONCE, INSPECTOR.
Inspector: BUT, SIR,
THIS MAN STOLE FROM YOU.
George: BUT FOR
PROVIDENCE'S HAND IN MY LIFE,
I MIGHT AS WELL
HAVE DONE THE SAME.
SELL THIS RING
IF YOU MAY EASE
YOUR FAMILY'S BURDEN BY IT.
WALK AN HONEST PATH HENCEFORTH,
AND I GIVE IT GLADLY.
Inspector: HE KNEW HE DIDN'T
OWE DARIO A DAMN THING,
AND HE TOOK DIO IN ALL THE SAME.
JoJo: FATHER, HANG ON.
THE DOCTOR IS ON HIS WAY NOW.
George: JOJO, DON'T HATE DIO
FOR WHAT HE'S DONE.
I AM TO BLAME FOR THIS.
I WAS HARD ON YOU,
BECAUSE YOU ARE A JOESTAR.
I WENT TOO EASY ON DIO, AND HE
MIGHT HAVE FELT I DIDN'T CARE.
PERHAPS HE DID THIS
FOR WANT OF A FATHER'S LOVE.
PLEASE, SEE THAT HE'S BURIED
NEXT TO DARIO.
JoJo: FATHER.
George: DON'T LOOK SO SAD, JOJO.
WHERE BETTER TO DIE
THAN IN THE ARMS OF MY SON?
♪
( JoJo sobs )
( thunder crashes )
Men: SIR JOESTAR!
Inspector: WE HAVE
LOST MUCH THIS NIGHT.
A NOBLE MAN'S SOUL
HAS BEEN TAKEN FROM THE WORLD.
( Speedwagon growls )
YOU'RE WRONG!
ALL THAT WAS GOOD IN THAT MAN,
HE PASSED IT ALONG TO JONATHAN,
EVERY BIT OF IT!
YOU CAN BE SURE.
JOJO'S GONNA LIVE
AN UPRIGHT LIFE
USING WHAT HIS FATHER GAVE HIM.
RICH FOLKS ARE RUBBISH.
WATCHING 'EM FLOUNCE AROUND,
I WANNA THROW THE WHOLE LOT
OF THEM INTO THE THAMES,
BUT NOT THE JOESTARS.
THEY'RE HEROIC
AND MERCIFUL AND JUST.
THE WHOLE DAMN LOT
ARE GIANTS AMONG MEN.
( gasps ) WHAT THE HELL?!
THE BODY!
DIO'S CORPSE, IT‐‐IT VANISHED.
‐ ( police gasp )
‐ ( thunder crashes )
Speedwagon: OI, COPPER!
AWAY FROM THE WINDOW!
♪
( inspector groans )
( sputters )
Dio: JOJO.
Policeman: THE INSPECTOR.
Speedwagon:
NO, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
HOW'S HE ALIVE?
Policeman #2: HE CAN'T BE.
WE ALL FILLED HIM
FULL OF BULLETS.
Policeman #1:
KEEP YOUR DISTANCE, LADS.
HE'S ARMED WITH SOMETHING.
♪
JoJo: WAS IT THE MASK?
Policeman #3:
HE'S COMING RIGHT AT US!
Speedwagon:
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
HIT 'EM WITH EVERYTHING
YOU'VE GOT LEFT!
JoJo: COME NO CLOSER.
♪
NOT ANOTHER STEP! I MEAN IT.
Speedwagon:
BLOW HIS BRAINS OUT NOW!
DO IT BEFORE HE KILLS US ALL!
♪
( JoJo gasps )
Dio: MMM.
( Speedwagon gasps )
SHOT 'EM IN THE HEAD, AND IT
DIDN'T EVEN SLOW HIM DOWN.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
WITH ALL THE LEAD WE PUT HIM,
HE SHOULD BE WORM FOOD BY NOW.
JoJo: HOW CAN THIS BE?
Dio: JOJO...
I SHOULD THANK YOU FOR
THE SOURCE OF MY NEWFOUND POWER,
YOUR FATHER'S BLOOD
AND THE ANCIENT MASK.
( hisses )
( policeman #1 gasping )
‐ ( Dio sighs )
‐ ( blood pumping )
JoJo: HE TAKES HIS VERY LIFE.
BUT HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
‐ DIO, YOU VILLAIN...
‐ ( all yell )
JoJo: WHAT SORT
OF MONSTER HAVE YOU BECOME?!
( Speedwagon gags )
( Dio sighs )
( Speedwagon groans )
JoJo: HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
THINK, JOJO. THINK.
THE KNIFE, FATHER,
BLOOD, DIO, THE MASK,
MY NOTES, THE BRAIN,
UNKNOWN ABILITIES,
UNKNOWN STRENGTH.
THERE IS NOTHING HUMAN
LEFT OF YOU, DIO!
( Dio chuckles )
( JoJo gasping )
FATHER.
♪
Speedwagon: DON'T DO IT, JOJO!
YOU HAVEN'T GOT
A CHANCE IN HELL.
I NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS, LAD.
HE BROKE THOSE COPPERS TO PIECES
LIKE THEY WAS BLEEDIN' TWIGS.
JoJo: I KNOW.
HONESTLY, I'M TERRIFIED.
ALL THE SAME, I CAN'T
LET DIO KILL ANYONE ELSE.
THIS DEMON MUST BE ANNIHILATED!
Speedwagon: PLEASE,
JOJO, I BEG OF YA.
HE'LL TEAR YOU APART!
JoJo: THAT'S IT.
ACCORDING TO MY RESEARCH
ON THE MASK,
IT WAS FABLED TO UNLOCK
THE BRAIN'S HIDDEN POTENTIAL.
TO VANQUISH DIO,
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS‐‐
( joints cracking )
( Speedwagon gasps )
( creature growling )
Speedwagon: THIS ONE'S ALIVE.
Creature: YOUR BLOOD,
IT SMELLS SO DELICIOUS.
‐ ( gurgles )
‐ ( Dio chuckles )
( Speedwagon gasping )
( creature laughs )
NOW I'M GOING
TO TURN YOU INSIDE OUT.
( roars )
( Speedwagon screams )
( JoJo roars )
( creature gurgles )
JoJo: HE WAS MY BROTHER.
LOOK AT HIM NOW.
FATHER, PLEASE LEND ME
THE STRENGTH TO DO WHAT I MUST.
( Dio sighs )
JoJo: COURAGE, JOJO.
DIO IS POWERFUL,
BUT YOU KNOW HOW TO END HIM,
AND END HIM YOU MUST!
Speedwagon: WATCH OUT!
( Dio roars )
JoJo: IT'S OVER.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET YOU
KILL ANYONE ELSE, DIO!
( Speedwagon gasps )
HE CAUGHT THE SODDIN' SPEAR.
RIGHT THROUGH THE HAND,
AND HE DON'T EVEN FLINCH.
NO WAY. THE HOLE FROM WHERE
I SHOT HIM IN THE HEAD,
IT'S HEALED UP.
THAT SPEAR AIN'T GONNA HURT HIM.
HE'S IMMORTAL.
( JoJo grunts )
YOU'RE SUCH A WEAKLING, JOJO.
( JoJo yelps )
( gasps )
Dio: ON YOUR FEET, INSECT.
I'VE YET TO GAUGE THE FULL
EXTENT OF MY NEW POWERS,
SO LET'S PLAY A LITTLE LONGER,
SHALL WE?
I TRUST YOU'LL BE
LONG SINCE DEAD
BY THE TIME I FIGURE THEM OUT.
HMM?
( chuckles )
HIDING, ARE WE?
HMM.
♪
( sniffs )
( trickling )
( chuckles )
( hisses )
YOU WERE A FOOL TO ATTACK ME.
I HAVE DISOWNED MY WEAKNESS
IN FAVOR OF LIFE EVERLASTING.
YOU'RE BEHIND THE CURTAIN,
LIKE POLONIUS,
AND, LIKE POLONIUS, IT IS THERE
THAT YOU SHALL MEET YOUR END.
( screams )
JoJo: NO ONE'S IMMORTAL,
NOT EVEN YOU.
( Dio growling )
( Speedwagon gasps )
HE'S ABLE TO HEAL FASTER
THAN THE FLAMES CAN HURT HIM.
IF THAT AIN'T IMMORTALITY,
THEN I'M THE QUEEN.
JoJo: FIRE HURTS HIM,
BUT NOT ENOUGH.
( Speedwagon gasps )
JOJO! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
JoJo: JUST GET TO SAFETY,
SPEEDWAGON.
IF DIO WANTS A FIGHT,
I MEAN TO GIVE HIM ONE.
♪
( Dio grunts )
( JoJo grunting )
Speedwagon: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU MAD?
THE FLAMES
ARE GONNA BOX YOU IN UP THERE.
( JoJo groans )
Speedwagon: JOJO,
YOU BRAVE FOOL,
I HOPE TO HELL
YOU'VE GOT A PLAN.
JoJo: I'M WAITING FOR YOU, DIO.
( Dio grunts )
( chuckles )
KNOW THIS. IT ENDS HERE.
I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU
TO LEAVE THIS MANSION ALIVE.
Speedwagon: NO, THAT'S LUNACY!
( yelps )
( groans )
Dio: LURING ME AWAY
FROM THE GUTTER RAT?
HOW VERY NOBLE OF YOU.
NO MATTER.
HAH.
I'LL DRAIN YOU DRY,
AND YOUR BLOOD WILL HELP ME MEND
FROM THIS LITTLE ADVENTURE.
YOU CLIMB THE WALL
IN VAIN, JOJO.
IN YOUR HASTE TO FLEE FROM ME,
ALL YOU HAVE DONE
IS GUARANTEED YOUR DOOM.
YOU WILL BE CONSUMED TONIGHT,
BY THE INFERNO BELOW OR BY ME.
( footsteps approaching )
FATHER.
FATHER, REST IN PEACE.
LET THE RISING SMOKE
GUIDE YOUR SOUL TO HEAVEN.
BUT FIRST, PLEASE,
LEND ME YOUR AID ONE FINAL TIME.
LET THE FIRE BURN
WITH YOUR STRENGTH.
Speedwagon: WHAT DOES HE MEAN
TO ACCOMPLISH UP THERE?
( gasps )
NO, THAT'S CRAZY!
YOU'RE THROWIN' YOUR LIFE AWAY!
DON'T DO IT! DON'T DO IT, JOJO!
( tiles cracking )
JoJo: ANY MOMENT NOW.
( Dio roars )
USELESS. YOU FIGHT
AS THOUGH YOU WANT TO DIE.
Narrator: IN THAT MOMENT,
JOJO'S SHORT LIFE
FLASHED BEFORE HIS EYES.
♪
( JoJo grunts )
MY LONELY YOUTH,
MY TIME WITH DIO.
YOU DID ME WRONG TIME AND AGAIN,
SO NOW I'LL SETTLE THE SCORE.
Speedwagon: THE LONGER
THE FIRE BURNS,
THE HOTTER IT GETS,
AND JOJO KNOWS IT.
HE MEANS TO USE THE MANSION
AS A FUNERAL PYRE
AND BURN THE DEVIL FASTER
THAN HE CAN REPLENISH HIMSELF,
AND NOW THAT THE HOUSE
IS HOT ENOUGH,
HE'S GONNA KNOCK HIM BACK IN.
JOJO!
( JoJo yells )
Dio: HOW DARE YOU LAY
YOUR HANDS ON ME, YOU INSECT?!
JoJo: THE ONLY HOME
I'VE EVER KNOWN
WILL BE IN ASHES
BEFORE THE DAWN.
FATHER IS DEAD, AND I AM ALONE.
I HAVE NOTHING LEFT TO LOSE...
BUT MY LIFE ITSELF.
WE GO TO THE FLAMES
TOGETHER, DIO!
I'LL GLADLY DIE
IF IT MEANS AN END TO YOUR EVIL!
( Dio scoffs )
DIE FOR NOTHING, FOOL!
( JoJo screams )
Dio: ALL I LOSE
BY YOUR SACRIFICE
IS THE BLOOD I WOULD HAVE TAKEN.
BLACKEN AND BURN AMONG THE BONES
OF YOUR DAMNABLE FATHER, JOJO!
I AM A GOD IN ALL BUT NAME.
WITH THE POWERS AT MY COMMAND,
I WILL RULE THIS WORLD.
THANK YOU, BROTHER,
FOR THIS GREAT BOON.
( JoJo screams )
DAMN IT.
DIO! I'M NOT DONE WITH YOU!
Dio: WHY WON'T YOU DIE ALREADY?!
JoJo: THERE'S NO ESCAPE, DIO.
YOU BROUGHT THIS DOOM
UPON YOURSELF.
THIS IS THE KNIFE
YOU USED TO KILL MY FATHER!
SO AS YOU DID TO THE MAN
WHO RAISED US BOTH,
I NOW DO UNTO YOU!
( Dio screams )
( JoJo grunting )
Dio: I'VE CRUSHED
HIS ARM BONES TO SPLINTERS,
AND HE'S ALREADY ABLAZE,
BUT HIS GRIP ON ME IS
STILL THAT OF A VISE.
SO BE IT, JOJO.
CONSIGN US BOTH UNTO THE FLAMES.
BUT PERISH KNOWING
I WILL SURVIVE THIS MOMENT.
FOR EVERYTHING YOU HAVE DONE,
EVEN THIS INFERNO
CANNOT DEVOUR ME!
JoJo: FATHER!
LEND ME YOUR POWER!
Narrator: HIS DESPERATE CRY
ECHOED IN THE NIGHT.
WHETHER URGED ON
BY HIS DEPARTED FATHER
OR HEEDING AN INSTINCT
BORNE OF A LONG FAMILIARITY
WITH THE HOME
WHICH BURNED AROUND HIM,
HE KICKED...
AND THAT PUT THEM
RIGHT IN LINE WITH...
( Dio sputters )
WHAT THE‐‐
Narrator: THE STATUE
OF THE JOESTAR FAMILY'S
GUARDIAN ANGEL.
( Dio screams )
HOW COULD A WORM LIKE YOU‐‐
( screams )
I‐‐I FORGOT
WHO I WAS DEALING WITH.
BLOODY HIS NOSE, AND HE
COMES BACK TWICE AS FIERCE.
JOJO!
I HAD SUCH PLANS
FOR THIS WORLD,
( fading )
SUCH PLANS...
♪
( JoJo grunts )
Speedwagon: JOJO.
JoJo: IT'S OVER.
Speedwagon: YOU'RE ALIVE.
YOU LUCKY BASTARD.
HE DID IT.
JOJO BESTED HIM!
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
( stones shifting )
( apothecary laughs )
THERE IT IS.
‐ ( screams )
‐ ( blood pumping )
( Dio exhales )
♪
Man: COURAGE IS TO LOOK
YOUR FEAR IN THE EYE.
Speedwagon: DIO'S EVIL, YEAH,
BUT THIS GUY IS FAR WORSE.
Man #2: PREPARE FOR THE CARNAGE!
Woman: WHO DO I LOOK LIKE?
JoJo: I BEG OF YOU,
TEACH ME HOW TO WIELD IT.