Father: POCO, WHERE YOU BEEN?
HOW DARE YOU LEAVE
THE HOUSE LIKE THIS?
( slap )
Poco: BUT PLEASE, PAPA.
( father panting )
Poco: PAPA, I'M SORRY
I LEFT THE HOUSE,
BUT WH‐WHERE'S MY SISTER?
Father: WELL,
WHERE DO YOU THINK?
SHE'S OUT LOOKIN' FOR YOU.
Poco: WHA?!
NO, PAPA. DON'T SAY THAT.
TELL ME SHE DIDN'T GO OUT.
Father: POCO, WHAT'S AILIN' YOU?
YOU'RE NOT BEHAVIN' RIGHT.
Poco: MY SISTER!
MY SISTER!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( sister gasping )
( creature laughs )
Dio: CONSIDER THIS, DEAR.
EXAMINE THIS ROSE IN BLOOM
FOR BUT A MOMENT,
VIBRANT, FRESH, AND YOUNG.
WHAT YOU SEE
IS A MIRROR OF YOUR YOUTH.
CONSIDER THIS FACT CAREFULLY,
MADEMOISELLE.
FROM THE FIRST MOMENT
THIS FLOWER FULLY BLOOMS,
IT BEGINS TO WITHER.
A SHAME, DON'T YOU THINK?
Creature: ONLY 16, SO SWEET,
SO INNOCENT AND PURE NOW,
SO FULL
OF DELICIOUS LIFE ENERGY.
WONDERFUL, LORD DIO.
( laughing )
( Dio scoffs )
( creature gags )
Dio: THOSE LACKING IN MANNERS
ARE NOT FIT TO EXIST.
NOW, MADEMOISELLE,
I OFFER UNTO YOU A CHOICE.
WOULD YOU NOT CARE TO ENJOY
YOUR YOUTH AND BEAUTY
FOR ALL ETERNITY?
FRET NOT, MY DEAR.
I SHALL NOT FORCE
MY FRIENDSHIP UPON YOU,
LIKE OTHERS MIGHT DO.
YOU CONTROL YOUR LIFE.
YOU HOLD YOUR DESTINY
IN YOUR OWN HANDS.
Sister: YOU FIEND.
Dio: EH? HOW'S THAT AGAIN?
( sister gasps )
YOU WEAR THE FLESH,
BUT YOU'RE NOT A MAN.
DEVIL, GO AWAY!
( Dio sighs )
( sister gasps )
( creature growling )
Dio: ALAS, ALTHOUGH
YOUR ACQUAINTANCE WILL BE BRIEF,
LET ME INTRODUCE MY COMPANION.
( creature growling )
Dio: I PRESENT UNTO YOU DOOBIE.
AS REGRETTABLY
I AM NOT TO YOUR TASTE,
ENJOY YOUR TIME WITH HIM.
AU REVOIR, MADEMOISELLE.
( Doobie hisses )
( sister gasping )
( screams )
( Doobie growls )
( sister screams )
( Doobie panting )
( chuckles )
OI! WHO HIT ME?!
WHO'S THERE?!
JoJo: DOESN'T MATTER, DOES IT?
YOU'RE A ZOMBIE.
YOUR KIND DON'T DESERVE
ANY INTRODUCTIONS.
Poco: SISTER!
Sister: POCO!
( Doobie hisses )
( yells )
( JoJo yells )
( Doobie laughs )
BIT YOU. BIT YOU
ON YOUR PRETTY LITTLE FACE!
‐ JoJo: WHAT DID THAT?
‐ Doobie: BIT YOU! BIT YOU!
WHAT'S HE GOT UNDER THERE?
Poco: HIS MASK. LOOK AT IT.
( Doobie laughs )
Sister: LOOK OUT!
Doobie: RUN, RUN, RUN.
( chuckles )
( Speedwagon gasps )
THAT ZOMBIE, HE'S CHOCK‐A‐BLOCK
WITH SERPENTS,
ALL SORTS, VENOMOUS COBRAS,
FLESH‐EATING ASPS AND VIPERS.
Doobie: BIT SURPRISED, ARE YOU?
Poco: THEY SANK THEIR FANGS
IN HIS FACE,
AND MORE THAN JUST ONCE.
( Doobie roars )
JoJo: HOW WEARISOME.
I HAVEN'T THE TIME
TO DEAL WITH ANY MORE
OF DIO'S FOOLISH GAMES.
Dire: DAMN. VERY WELL DONE.
HE SQUEEZED OUT THE POISON.
GOOD CONTROL.
HE'S LEARNED A GREAT DEAL
ABOUT BLOOD FLOW
IN A VERY SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME.
Speedwagon: BARON ZEPPELI,
HE'S HELPIN' OUR BOY
AFTER GIVING JONATHAN
HIS LIFE ENERGY WHEN HE DIED.
JoJo: I'LL USE A BIT
OF THE GREAT HAMON I POSSESS
TO TURN THESE SERPENTS
BACK ON THEIR MASTER.
( Doobie screaming )
Poco: SISTER!
Sister: POCO!
( both laughing )
♪
( Speedwagon grunts )
( JoJo grunts )
( footsteps )
♪
( Dio gasps )
JoJo: GUESS WHO SURVIVED
HIS TIME IN HELL, DIO.
Dio: YOU ARE ALIVE, JOJO.
CURIOUS.
I SUPPOSE LOGICALLY
THAT WOULD THEN INDICATE
YOU HAVE KILLED MY TWO KNIGHTS.
Creature: LORD DIO,
WE AWAIT YOUR ORDER
TO REDUCE HIM
TO A PILE OF BLOODY FLESH.
Creature #2: LORD, LET MY FANGS
MAKE AN IMPRESSION ON HIM.
JoJo: DIO!
Dio: NO.
THIS ONE IS FOR ME.
HE FALLS BY MY HAND ALONE.
DON'T MISUNDERSTAND ME, JOJO.
HONESTLY THIS IS SOMETHING
IN WHICH I WILL TAKE
NO PLEASURE.
WE WERE RAISED
IN THE SAME HOUSE,
AND THE PROSPECT OF TURNING YOU
INTO AN UNDEAD THING
IS NOT A HAPPY ONE FOR ME.
THAT'S WHY I WANTED YOU
TO BE QUICKLY DISPATCHED
BY MY KNIGHTS.
( JoJo breathes deeply )
Dio: BUT IT WOULD SEEM,
IN THE END,
I UNDERESTIMATED YOU.
SEEING YOU HERE ALIVE
BRINGS ME TO THE REALIZATION
THAT, AS AN EMPEROR,
I WAS BEING FAR TOO SOFT.
BUT NOW,
NOW I'LL PUT YOU TO DEATH
WITHOUT A MOMENT'S THOUGHT
OR COMPUNCTION.
JoJo: I COULD SAY THE SAME.
I WILL FEEL NO HINT OF GUILT
FOR YOUR DEATH.
Dio: BUT FIRST
I HAVE A QUESTION, JOJO.
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO THAT
MUSTACHIOED CHARLATAN OF YOURS?
YOU SEEM TO HAVE LOST HIM.
JoJo: HEAR ME, DIO.
IT SHAMES ME
AS A GENTLEMAN TO SAY THIS,
BUT I CAN NO LONGER
HOLD BACK THE TRUTH.
I, JONATHAN JOESTAR,
HAVE SUCH HATRED FOR YOU,
VENGEANCE CONSUMES ME.
I SWEAR I WILL KILL YOU!
( Dio chuckles )
COME, JOJO!
♪
( JoJo yells )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Dire: JOJO, PLEASE STEP ASIDE.
I HAVE A PRIOR CLAIM.
IT IS MY RIGHT
TO AVENGE MY FRIEND'S KILLING.
ZEPPELI WAS A BRAVE MAN
AND BOON COMPANION
THROUGH TWO DECADES
OF HARSH TRAINING.
DIO, FOR HIS LIFE,
I SHALL NOW SEND YOU
TO THE BOWELS OF HELL ITSELF.
JoJo: NO. WAIT, DIRE.
LISTEN TO ME.
DIO HAS HIDDEN ABILITIES
FOR WHICH YOU ARE NOT PREPARED.
( gasps )
Dio: HMM? AH.
THERE'S AN INTERESTING WALK.
APPARENTLY WITH DECADES
OF THE PROPER TRAINING,
MERE HUMANS
CAN ENABLE THEMSELVES
TO FLOAT THROUGH THE AIR.
BUT IN ONLY A SINGLE NIGHT,
I ATTAINED POWER FAR SURPASSING
THAT OF ANY HUMAN GURU.
( laughs )
YOU TRULY THINK YOU CAN
DEFEAT ME IN THIS MANNER,
LIKE YOU WERE SLEEPWALKING?
( yells )
( gasps )
Dire: FELL FOR IT,
DIDN'T YOU, FOOL?
THUNDER CROSS SPLIT ATTACK!
Speedwagon: UNCANNY.
IN CROSSING HIS ARMS,
HE CAN MOUNT AN ATTACK
WHILE STILL KEEPING
HIS GUARD UP FOR PROTECTION,
AN INCREDIBLE STRATEGY.
Straizo: NO FIGHTER HAS EVER
BEEN ABLE TO ESCAPE THIS MOVE.
♪
( all gasp )
Speedwagon: OH, NO!
Dio: USELESS! USELESS!
USELESS! USELESS!
Dire: I CAN'T‐‐I CAN'T MOVE.
( JoJo gasps )
HE FROZE DIRE.
Speedwagon: DIO MUST
HAVE SOMEHOW CHILLED
ALL THE MOISTURE
IN HIS BODY AT ONCE,
TURNING HIM TO ICE
IN AN INSTANT.
DIRE CAN'T CONTROL HIS HAMON.
HE CAN'T SEND IT INTO DIO
UNLESS HIS BLOOD IS FLOWING.
'STREWTH, THAT DIO'S A FEARSOME
CREATURE RIGHT ENOUGH.
HE FROZE DIRE'S WHOLE BODY
AT ONCE.
Dire: HOW DID YOU DO THIS?
Dio: OH, WE ARE FEEBLE,
AREN'T WE?
YOU IMBECILE, YOU DARE THINK
YOU COULD LAY A FINGER ON ME?!
( laughs )
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S GOING
TO GIVE UP YOUR LIFE
LIKE SOME MONGREL.
LET'S ENDEAVOR TO GIVE THEM
A GOOD SHOW, SHALL WE?
‐ Straizo: NO. DIRE, NO!
‐ JoJo: DIO, STOP IT NOW!
( Dire screams )
( all gasp )
( JoJo gasps )
Dio: IT'S TIME, JOJO.
YOU'RE THE NEXT
I SHALL DISPATCH TO OBLIVION.
( Dire growls )
( JoJo gasps )
Straizo: DIRE!
( Dire chuckles )
THOSE HAMON‐FILLED ROSE'S THORNS
DO STING A BIT.
( chuckles )
‐ Straizo: DIRE!
‐ JoJo: DIRE!
( Dio growls )
INSECT. HOW DARE‐‐
HOW DARE YOU WOUND ME,
WOUND MY FACE?!
JoJo: DIRE, NO.
( sputters )
SPEEDWAGON, MY SWORD.
Speedwagon: CATCH!
♪
JoJo: DIO!
I KNOW EXACTLY
HOW TO DEAL WITH YOU.
DIRE GAVE UP HIS LIFE,
WHICH SHOWED ME
JUST HOW VULNERABLE YOU ARE.
IT WILL BE VERY EASY FOR ME NOW.
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO STOP IT.
ALL I NEED TO DO IS FILL
BLUEFORD'S SWORD OF LUCK
AND PLUCK WITH HAMON
AND SLICE YOU WITH IT.
( Dio gasps )
Dio: YOU DARE TO TOUCH ME,
FILTHY HUMAN?
YOU DARE TO TOUCH ME
WITH YOUR HAMON,
MORE DISGUSTING
THAN FROG URINE?!
YOUR STRING OF LUCK'S RUN OUT.
( hisses )
NOW SHALL YOU BE FODDER
FOR MY ZOMBIES.
THEY WILL GNAW THE FACES
RIGHT OFF YOUR SKULLS.
Speedwagon: NOW WE SEE.
HE SHOWS HIS TRUE COLORS
AS SOMEONE FIT ONLY
TO RULE OVER A DUNG HEAP.
HIS COOL TOFF'S SOPHISTICATION,
NOTHING BUT A CHEAP MASK.
NOW THAT HE'S HAD HIMSELF A NICE
HUMILIATING TASTE OF HAMON,
HE REVEALS
HIS TRUE FILTHY SELF.
‐ ( zombies growling )
‐ ( both gasping )
Straizo: STRAIZO'S MY NAME.
NO MERCY.
Page: PAGE WOULD BE MY NAME.
Jones: JONES.
Plant: PLANT.
Bonham: BONHAM.
Zombies: NEEDLE VEIN STRIKE!
( zombies yell )
Straizo: ROSES ARE
ALIVE AND VITAL,
SO HAMON
WILL REMAIN INSIDE THEM,
FLOWING ALONG
WITH THEIR LIFE FORCE,
BUT THE SAME THING
CAN NOT BE SAID FOR STEEL.
( zombies screaming )
Straizo: IT'S NECESSARY
TO MAKE CONTACT.
( zombies growling )
Tonpetty: A GREAT MANY OF THEM
ARE COMING.
IF YOU WISH,
I SHALL HANDLE THEM FOR YOU.
♪
Speedwagon: FROM ALL
THE INDICATIONS I'VE SEEN,
THAT BLOKE DIO'S
MORE SWIFT THAN ANY LEOPARD.
( Dio hisses )
Speedwagon:
BUT WITH ZEPPELI'S HAMON,
JONATHAN JUST MIGHT KEEP UP.
( JoJo growls )
Speedwagon: THOUGH DIO
IS STRONG ENOUGH
TO PULVERIZE FLESH AND BONE
WITH A FLICK OF HIS WRIST.
FOR THE BOTH OF THEM,
IT COULD BE UP TO WHAT HAPPENS
IN THE VERY FIRST MOMENT.
( Dio grunts )
( JoJo grunts )
‐ ( Dio yells )
‐ ( JoJo breathes deeply )
Dio: I WILL SQUEEZE THE LIFE
OUT OF YOU WITH MY OWN HANDS.
JoJo: I WILL CLEANSE THE WORLD
OF YOUR EVIL INFLUENCE!
Dio: WHAT?
HE SNATCHED UP SOME ROSES
WHEN I WASN'T LOOKING.
( growls )
JoJo: COME NOW!
Speedwagon: WAIT. THAT'S GOOD.
HE CIRCLED AROUND TO THE RIGHT.
DIO IS BLIND ON THAT SIDE.
JoJo: TAKE THIS, DIO!
Dio: NO! DAMN IT ALL!
HE KNOWS EXACTLY
WHAT HE'S DOING!
( Dio screaming )
( JoJo yells )
Speedwagon: YES! KILL HIM!
Speedwagon:
HE FINALLY DEFEATED DIO!
( Dio sputters )
DEFEATED?
YOU FOOLS.
Speedwagon: OH, NO.
JoJo: I‐I CAN'T MOVE.
I'M FROZEN.
Dio: YOU'RE SO FEEBLE, JOJO.
( laughs )
NOW, WEAKLING, YOU SHALL JOIN
MY OTHER CHILDREN OF THE NIGHT.
( heart beating )
I'VE GOT YOUR
RUBBERY LITTLE CAROTID
BETWEEN MY FINGERS.
SO WARM AND SPRINGY.
A STRANGELY PLEASANT FEELING.
JoJo: A‐‐A KICK.
♪
( gasps ) MY LEGS
HAVE BEEN FROZEN, TOO.
Dio: USELESS! USELESS!
USELESS! USELESS!
ENJOYING THIS ANGUISH, JOJO?
ONE TINY LITTLE MOVE,
AND THIS DELICATE BLOOD VESSEL
SNAPS IN TWO LIKE A WET RIBBON.
WITH YOUR CAROTID OPEN,
ALL YOUR BLOOD WILL BE MINE.
THEN I SHALL FILL THE VACANCY
WITH MY OWN VAMPIRIC ESSENCE,
AND YOU WILL BE MY THRALL.
Speedwagon: WE HAVE TO HELP HIM.
Dio: ZOMBIES, TO ME!
KEEP THOSE PEASANTS BACK.
I'M RATHER BUSY.
Tonpetty: NOTHING SEEMS TO STEM
THIS TIDE OF ZOMBIES.
Straizo: WE CANNOT
PROVIDE ANY HELP.
Dio: NOW, JOJO, IN YOUR
LAST MOMENT OF FREE WILL,
REALIZE THAT THE VICTORY
WAS MINE.
JoJo: NO, DIO.
YOU'VE NOT WON YET.
YOU'VE MADE A FATAL MISTAKE.
Dio: HOW SO?
( JoJo laughs )
YOU SEE, DIO,
IF YOU FREEZE ME COMPLETELY,
YOU'LL NOT BE ABLE TO CONTINUE
FEEDING ON MY LIFE ENERGY.
THIS MEANS, HOWEVER,
THAT MY HAMON IS UNAFFECTED.
YOU CAN'T BLOCK IT AS LONG
AS I REMAIN PARTIALLY UNFROZEN.
YOUR TACTICS, TO SAY THE LEAST,
ARE SOMEWHAT FLAWED.
( Dio gasps )
HOW LONG HAS THE SWORD
BEEN IN THOSE FLAMES?
THE METAL BLADE IS
CONDUCTING HEAT FROM THE FIRE
FASTER THAN I CAN FREEZE IT.
HAMON IS FLOWING UP THE BLADE.
JoJo: SUNLIGHT
YELLOW OVERDRIVE!
NOW!
Speedwagon: HE'S DONE IT!
HUH?
Tonpetty: NOT EXACTLY CORRECT.
IT'S QUITE EVIDENT THE HAMON
DID NOT MAKE IT THROUGH.
JoJo: MY ARM.
MY ARM IS FROZEN SOLID AGAIN!
I ONLY BRIEFLY
TOUCHED HIS FACE.
Dio: THIS ISN'T OVER, JOJO.
♪
I HAVE TO ADMIT I MUST ADMIRE
YOUR TENACIOUSNESS.
REALLY, I DO.
AND YOUR INGENIOUS USE
OF THE FLAME,
TRULY MARVELOUS EXAMPLE
OF QUICK THINKING.
HMM.
BUT REALLY, JOJO,
AN EMPEROR'S REACH
SHOULD EXCEED HIS GRASP.
JUST A TOUCH ON THE ARM
IS ALL IT TAKES.
I CAN TURN YOUR WHOLE BODY
TO ICE IN TWO SECONDS.
( JoJo grunting )
Speedwagon: THE VAMPIRE ESSENCE,
HE SQUEEZED IT OUT.
HE'S NOT DONE.
JONATHAN WON'T GIVE UP.
Dio: REALLY?
THE "LET'S DO BATTLE" STANCE?
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
NO MATTER HOW YOU PREPARE,
HUMAN ABILITY IS
EXTREMELY LIMITED AND FINITE.
YOUR HAMON TRAINING
AVAILS YOU NOTHING.
IT'S USELESS, USELESS, USELESS,
USELESS, USELESS, USELESS!
A MERE MONKEY
CAN NEVER DEFEAT A LION.
IN COMPARISON TO MY POWER,
YOU ARE BUT A MERE MONKEY, JOJO!
JoJo: YOU'RE WRONG!
WITH TRUE CONVICTION,
THE HUMAN RACE
CAN OVERCOME ANYTHING!
LET ME DEMONSTRATE TO JUST WHAT
HEIGHTS A HUMAN BEING CAN RISE.
Dio: DON'T WASTE YOUR TIME.
A ZOMBIE IS ALL YOU'LL EVER BE!
( yells )
( JoJo breathes deeply )
Speedwagon: 'STREWTH!
HIS HAND IS BURNING!
FLAME'S COMING FROM HIS GLOVE.
THAT MIGHT JUST HAVE THE POWER
TO GET THROUGH DIO'S ICE.
JoJo: WHEN THIS BUSINESS
IS DONE,
WHICH ONE OF US
WILL HAVE FALLEN?!
WE'LL FIND OUT, DIO!
( yelling )
( Dio yelling )
( all gasp )
Tonpetty: DIO'S BLOCKING JOJO.
BUT, NO...
IT'S BREAKING THROUGH.
♪
( Dio screams )
I'M DISINTEGRATING.
IT CAN'T BE!
( gagging )
THE PAIN. THE BURNING.
I CAN'T‐‐
( gagging )
MY REIGN WAS
TO HAVE LASTED FOREVER,
FOR CENTURIES UNCOUNTED BY MAN.
JoJo: YOU HAD
TO BE DESTROYED, DIO.
Dio: I WILL NOT DIE!
( JoJo gasps )
( zombies gag )
♪
JoJo: HOW DID‐‐
HE SHOT ENERGY
FROM OUT OF HIS EYE.
HE CAME
TO WITHIN ONLY MERE INCHES
OF INCINERATING MY BRAIN!
( Speedwagon gasps )
FAR TOO CLOSE.
Straizo: THE LAST ACT.
THE DEMON REFUSES
TO ACKNOWLEDGE HIS DEATH.
Speedwagon: DIO HAS FALLEN
FROM THE PARAPET.
( Dio screaming )
♪
JoJo: DIO.
( Poco gasps )
LOOK! HE FAINTED!
Speedwagon: HE'S WORN OUT.
TOO RIGHT. HE'S BEEN
IN MORE FATAL FIGHTS TONIGHT
THAN A MAN SHOULD HAVE
IN A LIFETIME.
Poco: BUT WHY
WOULD HE SHED TEARS
FOR AN EVIL CREATURE LIKE THAT?
Speedwagon: HE WEEPS
BECAUSE THEY SPENT
THEIR YOUTH TOGETHER.
DIO WAS LIKE A BROTHER TO HIM.
BUT AS FOR ME,
I COULD SING A SONG OF JOY.
BARON ZEPPELI,
WERE YOU WATCHING?!
HE DID IT!
JONATHAN JOESTAR DID IT.
DIO IS DEAD.
IT MAY SOUND AN EXAGGERATION,
BUT JOJO
SAVED THE WORLD TONIGHT!
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ WITH YOU
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
( vocalizing )
♪
Speedwagon:
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL SIGHT.
Erina: THESE TEARS
THAT I'M CRYING ARE FROM JOY,
JoJo: YOU MUST LEAVE, ERINA.
Erina: I WANT TO STAY LIKE THIS.
Dio: WHERE IS MY BODY?