Narrator: CAESAR WAS
THE SON OF MARIO ZEPPELI,
CONSIDERED THE BEST FURNITURE
MAKER IN ALL OF NAPLES.
MARIO WAS A PROPER
ITALIAN MAN OF HIS DAY,
THOROUGHLY DEDICATED
TO HIS FAMILY.
TO CAESAR,
HE WAS THE IDEAL MAN.
WHEN CAESAR WAS 10,
MARIO SUDDENLY LEFT
WITHOUT SO MUCH AS A WORD.
HAVING LOST THEIR MOTHER
YEARS BEFORE, THEY WERE ALONE.
DISTANT RELATIVES
STOLE WHAT LITTLE THEY HAD.
CAESAR BECAME A DELINQUENT,
GROWING TO HATE HIS FATHER
AND WHAT HE HAD DONE TO THEM.
( Caesar groans )
I BET HE'S LIVING CAREFREE
WITH SOME HOT YOUNG WOMAN!
I'LL GONNA FIND HIM
AND THEN KILL HIM!
Narrator: HE THREW AWAY
HIS YOUTH AND HIS FUTURE.
HE COMMITTED THEFT,
ARSON, ASSAULT,
ANYTHING SHORT
OF OUTRIGHT MURDER.
EVEN THE LOCAL MAFIOSOS
FEARED HIM.
Man: HEY, YOU'RE THAT GUY
NAMED CAESAR, AREN'T YOU?
SO WHAT'S YOUR LAST NAME?
Caesar: I DON'T HAVE ONE.
( man laughs )
WELL, THAT MEANS
THERE'S NO WAY YOU'RE ITALIANO.
ITALIANOS ARE PROUD
OF THEIR FAMILY NAMES.
Narrator: NEVER HOLDING BACK,
HE OFTEN STARTED STARTED FIGHTS
BY USING A WRENCH
TO SUDDENLY BASH
HIS OPPONENT'S HEAD
BEFORE CALMLY
FINISHING THEM OFF.
THOUGH HE DIDN'T KNOW IT YET,
HE WAS ALREADY
BEGINNING TO USE HAMON.
THEN, AT AGE 16 IN ROME...
( Caesar gasping )
♪
THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
IT'S REALLY HIM.
Narrator: AT THAT MOMENT,
CAESAR FELT HE MIGHT MURDER
HIS OWN FATHER.
BUT THEN...
( Caesar gasps )
W‐WHAT IS ALL THAT?
HUH?
THAT'S A MASSIVE DIAMOND.
Mario: NO!
BOY, DON'T TOUCH THAT STONE!
Caesar: IT'S YOU!
( gasps )
W‐WHAT THE HELL
IS THE WALL DOING?
( Mario screams )
( Caesar grunts )
Mario: STAY BACK.
THIS IS ALL A TRAP.
( gags )
Narrator: EVENTS HAD
OCCURRED 50 YEARS AGO
THAT WERE COMPLETELY UNKNOWN
TO CAESAR.
HIS GRANDFATHER WILL
HAD DIED TRAGICALLY
WHILE ON AN EXPEDITION.
MARIO TOOK UP HIS FATHER'S TORCH
AND TRAINED WITH HAMON
TO PREPARE,
DISCOVERING THE RUINS
SOON AFTER.
HE BEGAN A WORLDWIDE SEARCH
FOR A WAY TO DEFEAT
THE MONSTERS WITHIN
AND UNLOCK
THE TREASURE THEY HIDE,
BUT CAESAR KNEW NONE OF THIS.
Mario: YOUNG MAN,
I BEG FROM YOU A FAVOR.
MAKE YOUR WAY TO VENICE,
AND SPEAK WITH A WOMAN
NAMED LISA LISA.
IT'S A MATTER OF LIFE AND DEATH.
SHE IS THE ONLY ONE WHO HAS
ANY CHANCE OF STOPPING THEM.
Narrator: PERHAPS BECAUSE
SO MANY YEARS HAD PASSED
AND CAESAR HAD GROWN,
MARIO DID NOT RECOGNIZE HIS SON.
Caesar: FA...
Narrator: CAESAR'S FATHER
HADN'T ABANDONED HIS FAMILY
‐ FOR SELFISH REASONS.
‐ Mario: HURRY! PLEASE FIND HER!
Narrator: HE'D LEFT IN ORDER
TO KEEP HIS CHILDREN SAFE
FROM THE NIGHTMARE
OF THE PILLAR MEN.
‐ ( blood draining )
‐ ( heart beating )
♪
( Caesar gasps ) FATHER!
( cries )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
JoJo: I SEE.
Lisa Lisa:
CAESAR'S MISUNDERSTANDING
LED TO A DEEP HATRED,
BUT THEN THAT CHANGED.
IT BECAME PRIDE IN HIS FATHER
AND HIS FAMILY.
SO CAESAR SOUGHT ME OUT
AND PICKED UP
WHERE HIS FATHER HAD LEFT OFF.
JoJo: HE'S GOING, BECAUSE HE
NEEDS TO AVENGE HIS FATHER.
FORGIVE ME, CAESAR.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO SPEAK ILL
OF YOUR BRAVE FAMILY.
IF YOU STILL WANT
TO GO CHARGING IN THERE
EVEN THOUGH YOU KNOW DAMN WELL
IT'S GOING TO BE A TRAP,
THEN YOU MUST HAVE FIGURED OUT
SOME WAY TO BEAT KARS.
CHANGED MY MIND.
SINCE YOU'RE GOING
IN THAT DERELICT HELLHOLE,
THEN I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU,
CAESAR ZEPPELI.
( Caesar grunts )
A SET OF FOOTPRINTS
LEADS INTO THE MANSION.
( gasps )
( wind blowing )
♪
( gasps ) WHO WAS THAT?
I SWEAR I SAW SOMEONE THERE.
AM I HALLUCINATING?
THERE IT IS!
IT'S NOT AN ILLUSION!
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?!
( male voice )
CAESAR!
( Caesar gasps )
HE VANISHED.
BUT I KNOW HE'S HERE, CLOSE.
HE'S WITHIN A FEW STEPS OF ME.
DOES KARS HAVE
SOME KIND OF NEW TRICK?
NO, THE SUN IS SHINING
TOO STRONG FOR HIM.
HE CAN'T BE OUT HERE
AND SURVIVE.
Narrator: THE CAT STANCE,
A FUNDAMENTAL ELEMENT
OF KUNG FU.
CAESAR HAS
NEVER HEARD OF KUNG FU,
BUT INSTINCTIVELY
BALANCES HIS STANCE
AS HE RELAXES HIS LIMBS,
READY FOR ATTACK
FROM ANY DIRECTION.
FOR HIM, IT IS NOT A TECHNIQUE,
BUT A REFLEX.
‐ Meshina: CAESAR.
‐ ( Caesar gasps )
Meshina: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
GOING IN THERE ALL ALONE
IS MADNESS.
Caesar: JUST STAY BACK,
INSTRUCTOR!
I CAN'T MOVE AT ALL,
LET ALONE GO RUSHING IN.
SOMETHING IS HIDING JUST INSIDE
THE ENTRANCE OF THE BUILDING.
Meshina: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I CAN'T SEE A THING IN THERE.
HUH?
A‐‐A SINGLE FOOTPRINT
JUST APPEARED.
Caesar: HE MUST HAVE JUMPED.
HE'S COMING AT US FROM ABOVE!
THERE!
WHAT THE‐‐
WAMUU!
( Wamuu growls )
( Meshina groans )
( screaming )
Caesar: INSTRUCTOR, NO!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
THAT GUY WAS WAMUU.
ARE HE AND KARS
INSIDE THAT MANSION TOGETHER?
BUT WAIT A MINUTE. HOW CAN WAMUU
COME OUTSIDE DURING THE DAY?
HE DID LOOK KIND OF GHOSTLIKE.
Wamuu: WHERE IS HE,
THAT INFURIATING
SMART‐TALKING UPSTART?
I HEAR TELL THAT JOJO
HAS LEARNED QUITE A BIT.
WHERE IS THE MAN
WHO KILLED MASTER ESIDISI?
Caesar: WIND.
WAMUU CAN CONTROL THE WIND.
THAT'S WHY
HE'S DIFFICULT TO SEE.
AIR'S COMING FROM PIPES
IN HIS CHEST.
HE'S ONLY SLIGHTLY VISIBLE
BECAUSE OF WATER VAPOR SWIRLING
IN THE FLOW AROUND HIS BODY.
I'VE GOT IT!
HE'S CLOAKING HIMSELF IN VAPOR
THAT HE'S GENERATING
FROM THE AIR,
AND THEN HE'S PUMPING IT
OUT OF THOSE PIPES.
IT'S REFRACTING LIGHT
LIKE A MILLION TINY PRISMS.
IT'S A SUIT
THAT BENDS LIGHT AROUND HIM,
PROTECTING HIM
FROM THE SUN'S RAYS,
THUS ALLOWING HIM TO BE OUTSIDE.
THAT'S WHY
HE SEEMS TO BE TRANSPARENT.
Wamuu: TOO BAD JOJO ISN'T HERE.
YOU ARE THE BUBBLE USER
NAMED CAESAR, ARE YOU NOT?
SIMPLY BY LOOKING
INTO YOUR EYES,
I CAN SEE
THAT YOU'VE ALSO LEARNED MUCH
THOUGH YOUR ORDEALS.
VERY WELL!
YOU ARE WORTHY OF DEATH
AT MY HANDS, BUBBLE USER!
( Caesar yells )
WE'LL SEE WHO DIES!
I FEEL LIKE I DID BACK THEN,
WHEN I WAS NA ÏVE AND POOR,
BACK WHEN YOU VICIOUSLY
TOOK THE LIFE OF MY FATHER.
AND NOW I'LL USE MY VICIOUSNESS
TO DESTROY YOU!
VERY IMPRESSIVE,
BUT DON'T THINK YOUR WIND
WILL BE ABLE TO JUST
BLOW MY BUBBLES AWAY.
SOME BUBBLES
GO RIGHT THROUGH WIND.
I'VE SIGNIFICANTLY UPDATED
MY GRANDFATHER'S HAMON CUTTER.
BUBBLE CUTTER!
HIGH‐SPEED ROTATION
TURNS THE BUBBLES
INTO A SALVO OF DEADLY DISKS.
HAMON ENSURES THEY WON'T POP
ALONG THE WAY.
Wamuu: HMM?
Caesar: THE WIND PROTECTING YOU
IS NOTHING MORE THAN A POCKET
OF EMPTY AIR TO THEM.
INSTEAD OF DEFENDING YOU,
IT'LL SUCK THEM IN.
( Wamuu screams )
I UNDERESTIMATED
HIS SKILL WITH HAMON.
IT IS FAR MORE
THAN I BARGAINED FOR.
Caesar: HEH.
Wamuu: NOW, HAMON‐USER...
Caesar: HOLD IT.
I WON'T LET YOU GO INSIDE.
GLIDING BUBBLE CUTTER!
NOW, WHILE YOU'RE
STANDING THERE STUNNED
AND HELPLESSLY OFF BALANCE,
I'LL GIVE YOU A HAMON KICK.
Narrator: BUT CAESAR WAS IN
FOR AN EXTREMELY BIG SHOCK.
IF YOU ARE TRIPPED,
YOU TRY YOUR BEST NOT TO FALL,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU NEED TO AVOID
SUNLIGHT IN ORDER TO SURVIVE.
‐ BUT WAMUU WAS DIFFERENT.
‐ ( Wamuu growls )
Narrator: HE BENT OVER BACKWARDS
AND ATTACKED.
( Caesar groans )
♪
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THAT BEFORE.
HE'S NOT JUST AN IMMORTAL
WITH INCREDIBLE STRENGTH.
WITH SENSES LIKE THAT,
HE'S A FIGHTING GENIUS.
BUT MY BUBBLE CUTTER
MUST HAVE INFLICTED
SEVERE DAMAGE ON HIM.
THE ADVANTAGE HERE IS MINE!
I HAVE A WAY TO TAKE YOU DOWN,
EVEN INDOORS.
MY NERVES ARE HONED
TO A RAZOR'S EDGE.
I CAN FEEL
DIFFERENCES IN THE AIR.
I HAVE THE ITCH
LIKE WHEN I WAS POOR.
MY BREATHING
IS RELAXED AND NORMAL.
I'M NOT SWEATING.
PERFECT HAMON CONDITIONS.
( gasps )
INSTRUCTOR MESHINA!
( Meshina groans )
‐ ( feet shuffle )
‐ ( Caesar gasps )
I SEE YOU'VE TAKEN OFF YOUR COAT
AND MADE YOURSELF READY, WAMUU.
( wind blowing )
JoJo: DAMN IT.
CAESAR AND MESHINA AREN'T HERE.
DO YOU THINK THEY
MIGHT HAVE ALREADY GONE INSIDE?
Lisa Lisa: NO. THAT'S HIS‐‐
THAT'S MESHINA'S ARM.
Caesar: NOW TAKE THIS!
BUBBLE LAUNCHER!
Wamuu: THAT'S NOTHING.
♪
Caesar: BUBBLE CUTTER!
RUNNING? HAH!
Wamuu: I WON'T RUN
OR HIDE FROM YOU!
( gasps ) HUH?
( Caesar breathes deeply )
( chuckles )
( Wamuu growls )
Caesar: BUBBLE CUTTER!
YOU'RE DEAD, WAMUU!
GLIDING BUBBLE CUTTER!
( Wamuu groans )
Caesar: WAMUU!
Wamuu: I'M FINISHED
WITH THESE GAMES.
YOU'RE THROUGH.
♪
DIVINE SAND‐‐
Caesar: WAIT A MINUTE, WAMUU.
STOP, AND LOOK AROUND.
Wamuu: HUH?
Caesar: MY BUBBLE CUTTERS
ARE NOW BUBBLE LENSES,
AND THEY'RE FLOATING
IN THE AIR ALL AROUND YOU.
AND THAT ENORMOUS HOLE
YOU KNOCKED IN THE WALL EARLIER
IS JUST LIKE THE OPEN SHUTTER OF
A CAMERA ON A BRIGHT SUMMER DAY.
THOSE LENSES,
THEY FOCUS THE SUNLIGHT...
INTO THE HOTEL.
Wamuu: WHAT?!
( screams )
Caesar: YOU CAN'T MOVE.
YOU'RE LIKE FILM,
A FROZEN IMAGE.
YOU'RE TOTALLY EXPOSED, WAMUU.
( Wamuu groaning )
( Caesar gasps )
TRYING YOUR VAPOR BARRIER AGAIN?
NOT THIS TIME.
NOW, WAMUU,
I'M GOING TO FINISH YOU OFF
WITH A DIRECT HAMON BLAST.
Narrator: ONE POINT
AT ONE MOMENT,
A TINY BLIND SPOT.
CAESAR'S BODY CREATED
THE BRIEFEST OF SHADOWS
AMID THE BLAZING WALL
OF SUNLIGHT.
WAMUU DIDN'T WASTE HIS CHANCE.
( Caesar gasps )
Narrator:
HE SHOWED CAESAR ONCE AGAIN
THAT HE WAS A FIGHTING GENIUS
AND A GENIUS OF STRATEGY.
Wamuu: WIND POWER,
DIVINE SANDSTORM!
♪
( both gasp )
JoJo: HUH? S‐SUCH DESTRUCTION.
Lisa Lisa: IT COULDN'T BE.
JoJo: IT'S WAMUU'S
DIVINE SANDSTORM.
I'M SURE OF IT.
Lisa Lisa: SO THAT MEANS
CAESAR IS....
( Wamuu chuckles )
YOU HAD GROWN SO MUCH
IN SO LITTLE TIME.
I'M SATISFIED.
I HAVEN'T HAD A FIGHT LIKE THAT
IN AGES NOW, WARRIOR OF HAMON.
( groans )
AND IT WAS A CLOSE ONE AS WELL.
IF THE WIND
OF MY DIVINE SANDSTORM
HADN'T HAD THE STRENGTH TO BLOW
YOUR BUBBLE SENSES TO OBLIVION,
I HAVE NO IDEA HOW
I WOULD HAVE STOPPED THE LIGHT
BEFORE IT DESTROYED ME.
AND EVEN IF THE MIGHTY
LORD KARS, WHO CANNOT USE WIND,
HAD BEEN THE ONE
TO FIRST NOTE YOUR PRESENCE
AND CONFRONT YOU AS I DID
AND FACED YOUR POWER‐‐
( groaning )
IF HE HAD PREVAILED,
HE MOST CERTAINLY WOULD HAVE
BEEN IN FAR WORSE SHAPE
THAN I FIND MYSELF IN NOW. HUH?
( Caesar panting )
Wamuu: ENOUGH.
YOU WILL NOT FIGHT AGAIN,
FOR YOU HAVE NOTHING LEFT
WITH WHICH TO FIGHT.
MY DIVINE SANDSTORM
HAS SHREDDED YOUR BODY
BEYOND ANY CHANCE OF SURVIVAL.
‐ ( Caesar yells )
‐ Wamuu: STOP.
‐ THE BATTLE IS OVER.
‐ ( Caesar panting )
Wamuu: YOU HAVE NO MORE HAMON
WITH WHICH TO CONTINUE. SEE?
YOU'VE ALMOST
COMPLETELY BLED OUT.
THAT MEANS YOU HAVE NO HOPE.
STOP, CAESAR.
GOODBYE. YOUR LIFE AND
ALL YOU ONCE WERE HAS ENDED.
( gasps ) WHAT?
( Caesar chuckles )
Wamuu: MY LIP RING
WITH THE ANTIDOTE,
WHY DID YOU TAKE IT?
Caesar: I‐I'M NOT AFRAID
TO DIE HERE...
BUT I AM A PROUD MEMBER
OF THE ZEPPELI FAMILY,
SO YOU SEE, IT'S IN MY BLOOD.
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
MIGHT MEAN ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
TO A DEMENTED,
INHUMAN MONSTER LIKE YOU.
MY FATHER DIDN'T RECOGNIZE ME,
BUT HE SACRIFICED HIS LIFE
TO SAVE MINE ANYWAY.
MY GRANDFATHER
GAVE HIS HAMON ENERGY
TO SAVE JOJO'S GRANDFATHER
RIGHT BEFORE HE DIED.
IT'S TRADITION.
( gags )
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
I‐I CAN'T LET MY LIFE'S FLAME
JUST SPUTTER OUT TO DARKNESS.
THIS IS
THE ZEPPELI FAMILY SPIRIT,
HANDED DOWN FROM THE PAST
TO ENSURE THE FAMILY'S FUTURE.
IT'S THE HUMAN SPIRIT!
JOJO, THIS IS
THE LAST OF MY HAMON!
TAKE IT FROM ME!
( both gasp )
JoJo: DID YOU HEAR THAT?
IT SOUNDED
LIKE CAESAR SCREAMING.
Lisa Lisa: YES, I HEARD IT.
OH, NO. CAESAR CAN'T....
JoJo: CAESAR!
♪
Wamuu: HE MADE
A BUBBLE FROM HIS BLOOD.
HE MUST HAVE USED EVERY LAST BIT
OF HIS HAMON TO MAKE IT.
BEFORE HE DIED,
HE SAVED IT FOR HIS FRIENDS
RATHER THAN USING IT
TO TRY AND DESTROY ME.
I'LL LET IT GO,
BUT NOT BECAUSE
I'M SENTIMENTAL ABOUT HIM.
HIS TALENT AS A FIGHTER
WAS UNDENIABLE.
HE HAS MY DEEP RESPECT
AS A FELLOW WARRIOR.
I WILL HOLD YOU AND THE LAST
MOMENTS WE SPENT TOGETHER
FOREVER IN MY MEMORY, CAESAR...
A MAN AS SPLENDID
AND AS FLEETING
AS THE BUBBLES HE CONJURED.
♪
( stones clatter )
JoJo: THE PLACE IS A WRECK.
A DIVINE SANDSTORM DID ALL THIS,
AND CAESAR WAS CAUGHT
RIGHT INSIDE THE HEART OF IT.
( both gasp )
A BUBBLE.
C‐COULD IT BE?
LOOK AT THAT.
INSIDE IS CAESAR'S BANDANA.
ALSO A RING,
WAMUU'S LIP RING.
( yelps )
THIS HAMON ENERGY
FEELS REALLY STRANGE.
W‐WHOA!
( gasping )
YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T
BEEN ABLE TO BRING MYSELF
TO CALL CAESAR'S NAME SINCE WE
MADE OUR WAY INTO THIS PLACE.
IT'S BECAUSE I'M AFRAID
THERE'LL BE NO ANSWER.
IF I CAME IN HERE
AND CRIED OUT HIS NAME,
THERE MIGHT NOT BE
ANY RESPONSE IN RETURN.
THERE MIGHT BE NOTHING
BUT A LIFELESS SILENCE.
THAT IS WHAT SCARES ME.
I COULDN'T ACCEPT IT,
SO I DIDN'T CALL HIS NAME.
‐ BUT NOW I KNOW HE'S GONE.
‐ ( man singing opera )
THE HAMON
CONTAINED IN THAT BUBBLE
TOLD ME EVERYTHING
I NEEDED TO KNOW.
RIGHT HERE,
JUST A FEW MOMENTS AGO,
CAESAR DIED.
GUH! CAESAR, YOU BASTARD.
YOU HAD TO BE A DAMN SHOWOFF
RIGHT UP UNTIL THE VERY END,
AND THEN YOU LEAVE
A PRECIOUS GIFT
LIKE THIS FOR ME.
CAESAR, WHERE ARE YOU?!
WHERE THE HELL
ARE YOU SLEEPING?
I'LL FIND YOU, CAESAR.
I'LL DIG YOU UP.
‐ CAESAR!
‐ Lisa Lisa: JOJO.
THIS ISN'T THE TIME
TO SEARCH OR GRIEVE.
‐ WE HAVE WORK TO DO.
‐ JoJo: WHAT?
Lisa Lisa: THERE ARE
TWO OF THEM AND TWO OF US.
THE NUMBERS ARE BALANCED.
THEY'RE EVEN.
THAT TRAIL OF BLOOD
LEADING UP THE STAIRS
TELLS ME THAT CAESAR
SIGNIFICANTLY WOUNDED WAMUU.
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF ENEMY TERRITORY.
LET'S GO FINISH THIS FIGHT.
JOJO, COME ON.
TAKE THE ANTIDOTE. THEN WE'LL
GO HUNT THOSE BASTARDS DOWN.
( JoJo scoffs )
THAT HEARTLESS‐‐
SHE CAN'T EVEN MANAGE TO SHED
A SINGLE TEAR FOR CAESAR.
( sputters )
♪
COACH LISA LISA,
YOUR CIGARETTE, IT'S BACKWARDS.
LISA LISA IS OUR COACH,
SO SHE ALWAYS HAS TO KEEP
A COOL EXTERIOR.
I KNOW SHE WANTS TO CRY
MUCH MORE THAN I DO.
HE TREATED HER LIKE A GODDESS
AND KNEW HER LONGER
THAN I'VE KNOWN HER.
I HAVE TO TRY
AND HOLD MY FEELINGS BACK.
CAESAR,
I KNOW YOU ALWAYS THOUGHT
I WAS IMPULSIVE
AND SELF‐CENTERED,
BUT SOMETIMES I DO UNDERSTAND
THE FEELINGS
OF THOSE AROUND ME.
I MIGHT FINALLY BE LEARNING.
I SWEAR I WILL FIGHT THEM
BOTH LIKE THE DEVIL
UNTIL THERE'S
NOTHING LEFT OF THEM.
I'LL AVENGE YOU, CAESAR.
YOUR SPIRIT IS WITH ME.
♪
BLOOD. HIS BLOOD.
THIS IS WHERE HE FELL.
CAESAR.
( Lisa Lisa crying )
JoJo: CAESAR!
♪
Narrator: THEY WERE DEEP
IN ENEMY TERRITORY.
KARS AND WAMUU WERE VERY NEARBY,
BUT THE TWO SIMPLY
COULDN'T HELP THEMSELVES.
JOJO CALLED OUT CAESAR'S NAME.
LISA LISA'S TEARS FLOWED FREELY.
BUT THEIR
HEARTBROKEN CRIES OF GRIEF
WERE ANSWERED ONLY
BY A COLD SILENCE.
CAESAR WAS GONE.
AS THEY MOURNED HIM,
THEY TOOK SOLACE
IN ONE SIMPLE FACT.
THOUGH HIS BODY HAD DIED,
HIS SOUL WOULD LIVE ON
THROUGH THEM.
REST IN PEACE, CAESAR ZEPPELI.
♪
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ THEY STAND THERE
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE
♪ AND I'LL BE THERE
♪
Lisa Lisa: YOU'RE REALLY
NOT IMPRESSING ME.
Vampire: I'M GOING
TO HUG YOU TO DEATH!
Wamuu: WE FIGHT TONIGHT
UNDER THE FULL MOON.
Kars: YOU HAVE NO TOMORROW.
JoJo: WE'LL FACE
THIS FIGHT TOGETHER, CAESAR.