♪
Narrator: LONG AGO,
AN ALREADY EXTRAORDINARY MAN
WISHED FOR FURTHER POWER.
THIS MAN COULD SOAR LIKE A BIRD,
SWIM LIKE A FISH,
BREATHE LIKE A TREE,
AND MOVE LIKE A WINDING STREAM.
BUT SUNLIGHT SPELLED HIS DOOM,
SO HE CREATED A STONE MASK.
ONE DAY, HE WOULD
FACE THE SUN WITHOUT FEAR,
AND THEN THE WORLD
WOULD BE HIS.
Kars: HMM.
( wind blowing )
Von Stroheim: WHERE'D HE GO?
PLEASE TELL ME
KARS FELL INTO THE LAVA.
( both yell )
( Kars screams )
I'M...
STILL ALIVE.
JoJo: ALL RIGHT.
( Kars groaning )
MUST CREATE ARMOR...
SOMETHING LIKE A CLAM...
OR A CRAB...
A BONY SHELL.
( grunts )
YES. MAKE ME IMPERVIOUS.
( both gasp )
( Kars groans )
( screams )
IT'S NOT ENOUGH!
JoJo: YOU DUMMY, THAT'S LAVA!
IT'S A THOUSAND DEGREES
IN THERE!
NOW BURN TO A CRISP,
YOU COCKY BASTARD!
( Kars screams )
Von Stroheim: OUCH.
JoJo: YES. THAT DID IT.
FINALLY.
KARS WAS THE LAST OF THEM.
THE PILLAR MEN ARE DEFEATED!
‐ ( Von Stroheim gasps )
‐ ( JoJo laughing )
( both gasp )
Von Stroheim:
THE SHOCK OF HIS DEMISE
TRIGGERED AN ERUPTION.
LET'S GET TO SAFETY
BEFORE WE CELEBRATE FURTHER.
JoJo: GOOD CALL.
HANG ON TIGHT, ALL RIGHT?
GUHH!
( Von Stroheim gasps )
( man vocalizing )
♪
( JoJo shudders )
( sizzling )
( gasps )
( screams )
( Von Stroheim shuddering )
( JoJo groaning )
( screams )
( Kars chuckles )
MUSIC TO MY EARS.
YOU PERFORM THAT ARIA PERFECTLY.
I'VE SO LONGED
TO HEAR YOU SING IT, JOJO.
( JoJo groaning )
Von Stroheim:
KARS, YOU'RE ALIVE.
A BIT OF HIS SHELL.
( mechanism whirs )
INORGANIC. BUT OF COURSE.
( Kars chuckles )
Narrator:
KARS FIRST COVERED HIMSELF
IN A SUBSTANCE
NOT UNLIKE A CRAB SHELL.
HOWEVER, IT WAS STILL ORGANIC.
IT WASN'T UP TO THE TASK.
FACED WITH THE HEAT OF THE LAVA,
IT BURNED AWAY INSTANTLY.
LUCKILY FOR KARS,
HE HAD THE IDEA TO CREATE
A SECOND LAYER OF ARMOR
MADE OF AN UNLIKELY SUBSTANCE,
‐ MERE AIR BUBBLES.
‐ ( Kars chuckles )
Narrator: THE BUBBLES MAINTAINED
A POCKET OF AIR
BETWEEN KARS'S BODY
AND THE LETHAL HEAT.
AS THE OUTER LAYER BURNED AWAY
WITH EACH PASSING SECOND,
MORE BUBBLES WORKED THEIR WAY
OUTWARD TO REPLACE THEM,
MAINTAINING
A PERFECT EQUILIBRIUM.
KARS HAD THE MOMENTS
HE NEEDED TO ESCAPE.
THE EARTH GAVE BIRTH TO LIFE,
BUT NOW, HORROR OF HORRORS,
KARS, A CREATURE OF THE EARTH,
HAS CONQUERED THE PLANET ITSELF.
♪
EONS AGO, LONG BEFORE MAN FIRST
THOUGHT TO CHRONICLE HIS DEEDS,
A GROUP OF CREATURES,
LIKE US, BUT NOT,
EVOLVED ALONGSIDE HUMANITY.
THE SUN WAS LETHAL TO THEM,
SO THEY LIVED OUT THEIR LIVES
UNDER THE COOL GLOW OF THE MOON
AND IN THEIR
SUBTERRANEAN CITIES.
EVEN WITHOUT
THE SUN'S SUSTAINING RAYS,
THEY ENDURED FAR LONGER
THAN THEIR HUMAN RIVALS
BY FEEDING
ON OTHER LIVING THINGS.
TO HUMANS THAT KNEW
OF THEIR EXISTENCE,
THEY WERE REVERED
AS GODS OR DEMONS.
THEIR NUMBERS WERE SMALL,
AS FEW DIED
AND CHILDREN WERE RARE.
IN ALL THINGS,
THEY MAINTAINED A VITAL BALANCE.
THEY KNEW NO STRIFE AND LIVED
IN PEACE WITH ONE ANOTHER.
BUT THEN...
A MAN OF GREAT PRIDE AND
AMBITION WAS BORN AMONG THEM.
Kars: STRENGTH IS HIDDEN
WITHIN THIS BODY,
TALENTS WE CAN
NAUGHT BUT DREAM OF.
I SHALL BE THE ONE
TO UNLOCK THEM.
Narrator: TO THAT END,
HE CREATED A STONE MASK.
THE MASK GRANTED HIM
UNHERALDED POWER,
BUT AT A TERRIBLE,
RAVENOUS COST.
TO SURVIVE, HE HAD TO CONSUME
LIFE AT A DIZZYING RATE.
IF LEFT UNCHECKED,
HE WOULD EVENTUALLY DEVOUR
EVERY LIVING THING ON EARTH.
HIS BRETHREN
BEGAN TO FEAR THE MASK,
AS WELL AS THE GIFTED SOUL
WHO CREATED IT.
Kars: HMM?
Male: HIS VERY EXISTENCE
IS A THREAT!
Male #2: THERE IS NO PLACE
FOR ONE SUCH AS HIM
IN THIS WORLD.
Female: AHH!
WE HAVE TO WIPE OUT HIS EVIL.
Kars: LOOK AT YOU FOOLS.
DON'T YOU WANT
TO HAVE DOMINION OVER THE SUN?
TO STAND IN ASCENDANCE
OVER ALL LIFE?
TO PURGE YOUR FEARS
AND REIGN FOREVER AS GODS?
♪
IF NOT, THEN DIE.
( all yelling )
Narrator: THE ICONOCLAST
BRAZENLY SLAUGHTERED
HIS BRETHREN,
EVEN KILLING THE PARENTS
WHO HAD GIVEN HIM LIFE.
HE AND HIS SOLE ALLY
TOOK THE TWO SURVIVING INFANTS
AND LEFT THE SCENE
OF THE CARNAGE.
THEY SET OFF
IN SEARCH OF ULTIMATE POWER,
A JOURNEY OF CONTINENTS
AND CENTURIES ALIKE.
AND NOW,
TEN THOUSAND YEARS LATER,
THAT POWER WAS
IN HIS HANDS AT LAST.
Von Stroheim: HE'S A GOD.
THIS TYRANT HAS BECOME A DEITY,
AND AGAINST SUCH A FOE,
THERE IS NOTHING THAT WE CAN DO.
WE MUST SUBMIT OR PERISH!
( JoJo groaning )
Kars: HMM?
HEAR THAT?
I THINK JOJO IS TRYING
TO TELL ME SOMETHING.
JoJo: HAMON OVERDRIVE!
Kars: WHAT? HAMON?
DID YOU SAY, "HAMON OVERDRIVE"?!
( JoJo screams )
Von Stroheim: JOJO!
( Kars scoffs )
( JoJo gasps )
NO. HOW?
MY LEG, IT'S MELTING AWAY.
THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE!
Von Stroheim: MELTING?
YOU DON'T MEAN TO SAY...
JoJo: IT CAN'T BE!
Kars: DENIAL WILL GET YOU
NOWHERE, MY FRIEND.
HAMON DID THAT.
I CONQUERED THE SUN ITSELF.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
THAT SOMETHING LIKE HAMON
WAS SOMEHOW BEYOND MY REACH?
JoJo: HUH? I JUST...
Kars: NOT ONLY
IS HAMON AT MY DISPOSAL,
BUT IT SEEMS THAT MINE IS
HUNDREDS OF TIMES MORE POTENT.
Von Stroheim: MEIN GOTT.
THAT MUCH STRONGER THAN JOJO'S?
IT'S AS THOUGH HE BRUSHED
HIS KNEE AGAINST THE SUN.
HIS FLESH IS LIQUEFYING
UND VAPORIZING
BEFORE HIS VERY EYES.
Kars: I WONDER, HOW DO YOU LIKE
THE TASTE OF YOUR OWN MEDICINE?
( JoJo groaning )
Kars: HMM.
A VERY ARTICULATE REPLY.
Kars: I SUPPOSE IT'S TIME
TO PUT YOU OUT OF YOUR MISERY.
Von Stroheim: JOJO!
JoJo: THIS IS IT.
I'M GOING TO DIE HERE.
THIS IS THE END.
Narrator: JOJO ACCEPTED
HIS IMPENDING DEMISE CALMLY.
HE FELT NO FEAR, NO PAIN,
NO REGRET AT HIS PLIGHT.
"I DID ALL I COULD,"
HE TOLD HIMSELF.
AS THE EPITOME OF EVIL
LOOMED OVER JOJO IN TRIUMPH,
HE WATCHED HIS DYING SELF
WITH PERFECT CLARITY.
STROHEIM FELT MUCH THE SAME.
UNABLE TO MOVE, HE KNEW
WHAT SNAKE PREY FELLS LIKE
AS IT STARES
INTO OBLIVION'S MAW.
( Kars breathes deeply )
THE POWER IN A BREATH.
( chuckles )
TO THINK I WILL ANNIHILATE
A PRACTITIONER OF HAMON
WITH HIS OWN DISCIPLINE.
♪
SURELY YOU CAN APPRECIATE
THE IRONY IN THAT.
JoJo: HA...MON...
( Kars yelling )
JoJo: STRONGER THAN MINE
HAS EVER BEEN.
Kars: LET ME BE THE FIRST
TO WELCOME YOU INTO OBLIVION!
JoJo: WAIT. HAMON.
( Von Stroheim gasps )
Kars: WHAT THE...
THE RED STONE!
Narrator: THE RED STONE OF AJA.
BUT WHY DID JOJO
BRANDISH IT AT KARS
IN THAT FINAL MOMENT?
EVEN HE HAD NO IDEA.
AS IF BY INSTINCT,
HE'D LUNGED THE STONE
TOWARDS THE APPROACHING HAMON
TO WHICH IT GRAVITATED.
( singing in Japanese )
NOW IN A MOMENT DEVOID OF HOPE,
JOJO'S BODY DID THE ONE THING
THAT COULD SAVE HIS LIFE.
HAVING SURVIVED
KAR'S COUP DE GRACE,
HIS WILL TO LIVE
SPRANG INTO ACTION.
JoJo: YES. THE RED STONE
AMPLIFIES HAMON.
Kars: HUH?
( gasps )
Narrator: FUELED BY
THE MAGNIFIED BLAST OF HAMON,
THE VOLCANO'S FURY
REACHES THE BREAKING POINT.
IT ERUPTS!
( Von Stroheim yells )
♪
WHAT? THEY BLASTED INTO THE SKY!
‐ ( JoJo groaning )
‐ ( singing in Japanese )
Kars: THE FORCE, IT'S STRONG,
LIKE NOTHING I'VE EVER KNOWN.
♪
DO YOU REALLY THINK
A LITTLE ERUPTION
WILL BE ENOUGH TO CONQUER
THE LIKES OF ME?!
I'LL JUST FLY MY WAY TO SAFETY.
ENJOY THE FRUITS
OF YOUR FOLLY, JOJO.
( gags )
JoJo: WHO'S LAUGHING NOW, HUH?
LET ME GUESS.
YOU'RE GONNA SAY, "DID YOU
PLAN THIS, TOO, JOJO? TELL ME."
Kars: HOW DO YOU ALWAYS KNOW?
Narrator: FOR A MOMENT,
KARS WAS DISTRACTED
BY JOJO'S ARM
AND HIS COCKY ATTITUDE.
THAT MOMENT WAS ALL IT TOOK.
SCALDING ROCKS
HE DIDN'T SEE COMING
LAUNCHED HIM EVEN HIGHER
INTO THE STRATOSPHERE.
( Kars screams )
DID YOU PLAN THIS, TOO, JOJO!
TELL ME!
JoJo: WHY ARE YOU EVEN ASKING?!
I SET THE TRAP,
AND YOU WALKED RIGHT INTO IT!
ALL OF THIS WENT DOWN
LIKE CLOCKWORK.
( Kars screams )
JoJo: I JUST GOT LUCKY,
BUT THINKING I OUTSMARTED HIM
WILL DRIVE KARS NUTS.
( laughs )
Narrator: AT THAT MOMENT,
THE ROCKS LAUNCHED
BY THE VOLCANO'S ERUPTION
REACHED ESCAPE VELOCITY.
KARS WAS THE PERFECT BEING.
NOTHING ON EARTH COULD KILL HIM,
BUT JUST THEN...
HE WAS BLASTED
INTO THE VACUUM OF SPACE.
Kars: NO! DAMN YOU!
Singer: ♪ JOJO
( music ends )
JoJo: IT'S OVER.
GRANNY AND STROHEIM,
OLD SPEEDWAGON, SMOKEY...
AND LISA LISA.
EVERYONE, GOODBYE.
Von Stroheim: NO.
JOJO!
Narrator: VON STROHEIM
MADE IT BACK TO THE OTHERS
EIGHT HOURS LATER, WHEREUPON
HE TOLD THEM THE SAD NEWS.
Kars: NO!
THE EARTH! NO!
DON'T PANIC.
JUST FIND THE EARTH.
I'LL USE AIR
TO CHANGE MY TRAJECTORY.
ONCE I'M BACK ON SOLID GROUND,
I WILL TEAR THAT BOY APART.
( groans )
( screaming )
NO! IT'S NOT WORKING!
I'M FREEZING.
THE AIR IS FREEZING AROUND ME.
THE MOMENT IT COMES OUT
OF THE JETS, IT TURNS TO ICE.
I CAN'T CHANGE MY PATH.
I CAN'T MOVE.
( screams )
Narrator: SO ENDED KARS,
LAST AND GREATEST
OF THE PILLAR MEN.
HIS BODY TURNED HARD AS ROCK,
AND HE FLOATED THROUGH SPACE
FOR THE REST OF TIME,
NEVER TO RETURN.
HE WISHED FOR DEATH,
BUT THERE WAS NOTHING OUT THERE
TO KILL HIM.
THE SPARK OF THOUGHT WITHIN HIM
WENT DIM AND THEN SILENT.
( bell tolling )
♪
Priest: WE COMMEND HIS SOUL
UNTO THE HEAVENLY FATHER.
THOUGH HIS LIFE ON EARTH
HAS ENDED FAR TOO SOON,
HE LIVES IN GRACE WITH YOU.
COMFORT THOSE
HE LEAVES BEHIND, O GOD,
AND LET THEM KNOW YOUR PEACE.
♪
Smokey: GOODBYE, JOJO.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU FOR TOO LONG.
COULDN'T HAVE BEEN
MORE THAN SIX MONTHS.
DON'T MATTER.
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE GONE,
I'M YOUR FRIEND...
FOREVER.
Speedwagon: COME, ERINA.
IT WON'T DO TO CATCH COLD.
LET'S GET YOU HOME.
Erina: JUST A BIT LONGER.
( JoJo laughs )
GUESS WHO.
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
JoJo: WHAT GIVES, FELLAS?
I FINALLY MAKE IT TO NEW YORK,
AND NOBODY WAS THERE
TO PICK ME UP.
THEN I GOT WORD
YOU WERE ALL AT A FUNERAL,
SO I DECIDED TO CRASH IT.
‐ ( both gasp )
‐ JoJo: HEY, LISA LISA.
GUESS YOU HEALED UP
PRETTY WELL, HUH?
MESHINA, GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO.
NEW HAND WORKS WELL,
THOUGH I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO ASK STROHEIM
IF HE CAN JAZZ IT UP
WITH A FEW GADGETS
OR TOOLS OR WHATNOT.
I GUESS THAT'S RIGHT OUT,
WITH US FIGHTING GERMANY.
Man: HEY, NOW.
YOU LEAVE THESE MOURNERS ALONE.
Man #2: THIS IS A FUNERAL.
SHOW SOME RESPECT, YOU OAF.
JoJo: OH, SO I'M AN OAF, AM I?
YOU NEED A LESSON IN MANNERS,
AND I'M GLAD TO OBLIGE.
Man #1: ALL RIGHT.
CALM DOWN. LET'S NOT BE HASTY.
‐ Meshina: BUT HOW?
‐ ( argument continues )
‐ Smokey: NO WAY.
‐ Man #1: HEY,
I'M TALKING TO YOU, BIG GUY.
YOU'D BETTER‐‐
JoJo: BACK OFF, MAN!
I'M JUST TRYING TO CATCH UP
WITH MY FAMILY AND FRIENDS.
All: JOJO!
( Smokey screams )
YOU'RE TELLING ME JOJO'S ALIVE?!
JoJo: HUH? YEAH, OF COURSE.
WAIT. WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
YOU'RE ALL STARING
AS THOUGH YOU'VE SEEN A GHOST.
I KNOW IT'S A FUNERAL AND A‐‐
HUH?
WHAT THE?!
WHAT'S MY NAME DOING ON THERE?
I'M ALIVE AND WELL!
WAIT. THIS FUNERAL WAS FOR ME?
Suzie Q: JOJO!
YOU'RE STILL RECOVERING,
YOU BIG SILLY.
DON'T RUN OFF IN THE RAIN
LIKE THAT.
( all gasp )
Suzie Q: HERE. TAKE THIS.
Meshina: HEY,
THAT GIRL IS SUZIE Q,
AND THAT‐‐THAT RING
LOOKS LIKE A...
( JoJo gags )
ARE YOU TELLING ME
YOU DON'T KNOW
THAT WE GOT MARRIED?
All: YOU GOT MARRIED?
Suzie Q: ISN'T IT CRAZY?
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
I'M OFFICIALLY
MRS. JOSEPH JOESTAR. GOODNESS.
( squeals )
IT MAKES ME BLUSH.
‐ ( sighs )
‐ JoJo: WAIT A SECOND HERE.
SUZIE Q, SOMETHING ABOUT THIS
DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT,
AND I WANNA KNOW WHAT.
THE ROCK I WAS ON
FELL INTO THE OCEAN,
AND ME ALONG WITH IT.
A FISHING BOAT PICKED ME UP.
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
YOU NURSED ME BACK TO HEALTH
IN VENICE FOR TWO WEEKS,
AND WE TIED THE KNOT.
SO WHY DID THEY
ALL THINK I WAS DEAD?
YOU NEVER SENT THAT TELEGRAM
LIKE I ASKED, DID YOU?!
Suzie Q: UH,
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
JoJo: TO ME,
THAT SOUNDS LIKE NO!
Suzie Q: UH...
( machinery clicking )
NOW, NOW. LET'S NOT GET
ALL CLICKY‐FINGERS.
I NEVER SENT IT!
‐ I'M SORRY, JOJO!
‐ ( JoJo groans )
SUZIE Q, WHAT THE HELL?!
YOU HAD ONE JOB, WOMAN,
ONE JOB!
‐ ( Suzie Q squeals )
‐ ( Smokey sobs )
JOJO CAME BACK TO US ALL!
Suzie Q: STOP IT!
I SAID I WAS SORRY!
JoJo: SORRY?!
THEY THOUGHT I WAS DEAD!
Lisa Lisa: JOJO.
Narrator: SOON AFTER, LISA LISA,
A. K. A. ELIZABETH JOESTAR,
TOLD JOJO
THAT SHE WAS HIS MOTHER.
THEY MOVED TO AMERICA.
IN 1948, SHE FOUND LOVE AGAIN
AND MARRIED
A HOLLYWOOD SCREENWRITER.
( Erina sighs )
Narrator: ERINA JOESTAR
CONTINUED HER WORK AS A TEACHER.
IN 1950, SHE DIED PEACEFULLY
AT THE AGE OF 81,
SURROUNDED BY FAMILY AND FRIENDS
WHO LOVED HER.
( Speedwagon chuckles )
Narrator:
ROBERT E. O. SPEEDWAGON
CONTINUED TO POUR HIS ENERGY
INTO PHILANTHROPIC RESEARCH,
HELPING TO FURTHER SCIENCE
AND MEDICINE IN COUNTLESS WAYS.
HE DIED IN 1952
OF A HEART ATTACK
AT 89 YEARS OF AGE.
A LIFELONG BACHELOR,
HE LEFT NO FAMILY BEHIND.
SMOKEY BROWN WENT ON
TO WORK HIS WAY THROUGH COLLEGE,
MAJORING IN POLITICAL SCIENCE.
LATER, HE BECAME
THE FIRST BLACK MAYOR OF A CITY
IN HIS HOME STATE OF GEORGIA.
MAJOR RUDOL VON STROHEIM
WOULD NEVER SEE JOJO AGAIN.
HE DIED IN 1943
AT THE BATTLE OF STALINGRAD,
A FEARSOME EXAMPLE
OF THE GERMAN SCIENCE
HE'D ALWAYS CHAMPIONED.
Von Stroheim: OUR TECHNOLOGY
IS THE GREATEST!
♪
Narrator: AND SO
THE YEARS FLOWED BY...
TO A NEW GENERATION.
AND AS FOR JOJO...
( JoJo groans )
Man: OH. RIGHT IN THE LEG, HUH?
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOU SHOULD WATCH
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
YOU WOULDN'T WANT
A BROKEN BONE AT YOUR AGE.
JoJo: YOU'RE RIGHT.
HOW CARELESS OF ME.
I GUESS THIS IS A CASE
OF LIVE AND LEARN.
HMM? HEY, WAIT A SEC.
YOU'RE JAPANESE, AREN'T YOU?
Man: I AM. WHY DO YOU ASK?
JoJo: IN THAT CASE,
WATCH YOUR DAMN BAG!
Man: YOW!
( JoJo scoffs )
( man groaning )
Announcer:
ALITALIA FLIGHT 285 FOR TOKYO
IS NOW BOARDING
OUT OF GATE C‐17.
( JoJo cries )
MY ONLY DAUGHTER
HAS BEEN MARRIED
TO A JAPANESE MAN
FOR OVER 20 YEARS,
FELL IN LOVE ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE WORLD,
AND NEVER CAME HOME AGAIN.
HER SON RARELY GETS TO SEE
HIS OWN GRANDFATHER!
THAT'S WHY I'LL NEVER
FORGIVE THE JAPANESE!
( man groans )
JoJo: THEN AGAIN...
THEY MAKE
SOME RATHER NIFTY GADGETS.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( waves lapping )
( man laughs ) ALL RIGHT.
IT'S FINALLY TIME TO HAUL IT UP.
Man #2: OH, MAN. WHAT DO YOU
THINK'S INSIDE IT, YOU GUYS?
Man #1: A HUNDRED‐YEAR‐OLD CHEST
LIKE THAT?
IT COULD BE ANYTHING.
Man #2: COME ON.
LET'S OPEN THAT BAD BOY.
♪