Narrator: TWO RINGS
FILLED WITH A FATAL POISON
HAVE BEEN IMPLANTED
AROUND JOJO'S NECK AND HEART.
NEITHER CAN BE REMOVED.
BEFORE THE RINGS DISSOLVE
AND THE POISON IS RELEASED,
JOJO MUST DEFEAT
THE POWERFUL WAMUU
IN ORDER TO SECURE THE ANTIDOTE.
JoJo: AHH! WHAT WAS I THINKING?
WHEN I SAID I NEEDED A MONTH,
I ONLY MEANT IT AS A BLUFF.
I DIDN'T THINK
HE'D TAKE ME SERIOUSLY.
I SHOULD HAVE SAID
I NEEDED A YEAR.
Caesar: A TIP FOR YOU, JOJO.
QUIT SCREWING AROUND,
AND ACT LIKE A MAN.
WE NEED TO THINK OF SOMETHING,
AND FAST.
JoJo: I KNOW.
THIS IS HOW I THINK.
BUT THERE REALLY ISN'T ANY POINT
IN ME THINKING
ABOUT THIS TOO HARD.
IF WE DO THAT, WE'LL REALIZE
JUST HOW MUCH TROUBLE
WE'RE BOTH IN HERE.
Caesar: ONCE YOU'RE DONE
WITH YOUR THINKING FREAK‐OUT,
I WANT YOU
TO PAY CLOSE ATTENTION
‐ TO WHAT I'M ABOUT TO DO HERE.
‐ JoJo: EH?
( gasps ) THE WATER'S
SUSPENDED IN MIDAIR!
( Caesar scoffs )
JOJO, CATCH.
TRY TO KEEP THE WATER
IN THE GLASS LIKE THAT.
EASY. I CAN DO THAT, NO SWEAT.
( gurgles )
Caesar: HERE'S WHAT
YOU DID WRONG.
THE STRENGTH OF YOUR HAMON
IS PRETTY MUCH
EQUIVALENT TO MINE,
BUT YOU WASTE
A LOT OF YOUR POWER,
BECAUSE YOU RELEASE IT
FROM THE PALM OF YOUR HAND.
( JoJo gasps )
Caesar: AND THUS
YOU CAN'T CONTROL THE WATER.
HOWEVER, WHEN I HOLD THE WATER,
I RELEASE HAMON FROM THE TIP
OF ONE OF MY FINGERS,
A SINGLE POINT.
THAT METHOD ALLOWS ME
TO FOCUS MY ENERGY,
MAKING IT EASY
TO CONTROL THE WATER.
SCATTERING HAMON EVERYWHERE
THE WAY YOU DO
JUST DISPERSES YOUR ENERGY.
THINK OF IT
LIKE USING A SQUIRT GUN
WITH ITS SMALLER HOLE,
RATHER THAN
AN OPEN WATER HOSE, CAPICHE?
( JoJo gasps )
Caesar:
YOU'RE NATURALLY GIFTED, JOJO,
BUT YOU NEED A LOT OF WORK
TO GET YOUR HAMON UNDER CONTROL.
I BROUGHT YOU TO VENICE
TO MEET MY MENTOR,
BUT IT'S GONNA BE A GRIND.
JoJo: OH, NO!
"GRIND" AND "WORK" ARE PROBABLY
MY TWO LEAST FAVORITE WORDS
IN THE ENGLISH LANGUAGE.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( JoJo sighs )
VENICE, HUH?
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
PRETTY MUCH A TOURIST TOWN.
WHAT'S A HAMON MASTER DOING
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
Caesar: EXCUSE ME!
DO YOU KNOW AIR SUPPLENA ISLAND,
AND HOW LONG
IT TAKES TO GET THERE?
GONDOLIER, DID YOU HEAR ME?
( JoJo gasps )
( gondola creaks )
♪
( gasps )
HOW IS HE STANDING
ON THAT OAR LIKE THAT?
UH, I DON'T THINK
I LIKE THIS, NOT ONE BIT.
( Caesar gasps )
( JoJo gags )
...THE HELL?
YOU ASKED FOR IT.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHO YOU ARE,
BUT I'M GOING
TO MAKE YOU PAY FOR THAT.
YOU'RE GONNA WISH
YOU NEVER MET ME.
Gondolier: AT LEAST
HE CAN CONTROL HIS HAMON
WELL ENOUGH TO STAND ON WATER.
THAT'S A START.
( Caesar gasps )
JoJo: A WOMAN.
IS THAT YOU, COACH?
Narrator: SHE GOES
BY THE NAME OF LISA LISA.
NOBODY KNOWS HER TRUE NAME,
HER PLACE OF ORIGIN,
WHERE SHE STUDIED, OR HOW
SHE MASTERED THE ART OF HAMON.
SHE WILL BE JOJO'S COACH
FOR AS LONG AS IT TAKES
OR AT LEAST
FOR THE NEXT MONTH.
JoJo: WELL, WELL. DON'T THINK
THAT I'LL FORGIVE YOU
FOR HITTING ME IN THE FACE
WITH THAT OAR.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE A GIRL,
DOESN'T MEAN THAT I WON'T
GIVE YOU WHAT YOU DESERVE.
Lisa Lisa: YOU SHOULD JUST
BE HAPPY THAT YOU IMPRESSED ME
WITH YOUR
INITIAL DISPLAY OF SKILLS.
WALKING ON WATER WHEN YOU
OBVIOUSLY LACK PROPER TRAINING
IS QUITE AN ACCOMPLISHMENT.
HOWEVER...
IF YOU TRULY WISH
TO MASTER HAMON IN A MONTH,
YOU MUST BE PREPARED
TO DIE FOR IT!
SHE‐‐SHE'S USING THE OAR
AS A HIGH BAR.
♪
( JoJo gasps )
( muffled grunt )
WHAT IS THIS? ( grunts )
Lisa Lisa: JOSEPH JOESTAR.
FROM THIS MOMENT FORWARD,
YOU WILL BE WEARING THAT
BREATHING CORRECTION APPARATUS
UNTIL I SAY OTHERWISE.
( JoJo gasps ) I CAN'T BREATHE.
Lisa Lisa: NOT WITHOUT
PROPER RHYTHM, YOU CAN'T.
HOWEVER,
WITH PROPER BREATH CONTROL,
YOU'LL HAVE NO PROBLEM.
IF YOU DO NOT MAINTAIN
PROPER BREATH CONTROL,
THEN, YES, THE MASK
WILL EVENTUALLY SUFFOCATE YOU,
SO FOCUS.
LEARN TO MASTER YOUR BREATH,
AND YOU'LL BE RUNNING MARATHONS
WHILE WEARING IT.
JoJo: ARE YOU CRAZY? GET THIS
DAMN THING OFF MY FACE RIGHT‐‐
( sputters )
I‐I CAN'T BREATHE.
Lisa Lisa: YOU DO REALIZE
YOUR TRAINING HAS ALREADY BEGUN.
YOU CAN TAKE
THE MASK OFF FOR MEALS
AND WHENEVER YOU NEED
TO BRUSH YOUR TEETH.
Caesar: JOJO,
DON'T MAKE IT HARD ON YOURSELF.
JUST KEEP YOUR RHYTHM
AND PRETEND THAT IT'S HALLOWEEN.
JoJo: I'M GONNA GET YOU, LADY.
Lisa Lisa: AND ONE MORE THING
BEFORE I FORGET,
SO WE'RE BOTH ON THE SAME PAGE.
I DID NOT ACCEPT
THE RESPONSIBILITY
OF TRAINING YOU JUST SO THAT
YOU CAN SAVE YOUR OWN SKIN.
I AM FORGING A SQUAD OF WARRIORS
CAPABLE OF ANNIHILATING
OUR ENEMIES.
JoJo: YOU‐‐YOU WITCH.
Lisa Lisa: CAREFUL. YOU WANT
ANOTHER GO‐ROUND WITH HER?
JoJo: HUMPH!
I WOULD NEVER HIT A WOMAN.
( Caesar laughs )
Lisa Lisa: IT'S ALWAYS
A PLEASURE, CAESAR.
AND YOU, JOJO,
WELCOME TO VENICE.
( JoJo thinking )
SHEESH.
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT RESPECT
HER HAMON SKILLS,
BUT GOOD LUCK FINDING ANYONE
WHO WOULD EVER MARRY HER,
EVEN IF SHE IS KINDA CUTE.
Caesar: BOW WHEN SHE LEAVES!
JoJo: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
ITALY'S MOST TRANSPARENT PLAYBOY
WANTS ME TO BE POLITE
TO THAT LITTLE WITCH?
Caesar: WATCH YOUR TONGUE, JOJO.
I RESPECT HER
LIKE MY OWN MOTHER.
SHOW HER THE SAME RESPECT.
I'M WARNING YOU.
( JoJo groans )
Caesar: AIR SUPPLENA ISLAND
IS ABOUT 30 MINUTES
NORTHEAST OF VENICE BY BOAT.
ITS MYSTERIOUS AIR
IS A STARK CONTRAST
TO THE CITY OF CANALS,
BUT IT POSSESSES A DARK BEAUTY
THAT SEEMS TO BE A PERFECT FIT
FOR LISA LISA.
THIS IS
YOUR NEW TRAINING GROUND, JOJO.
Lisa Lisa: I HAVE CLAIMED
THAT ENTIRE ISLAND AS MY HOME.
JoJo: SO THIS IS WHERE I'LL HAVE
TO DIE FOR MY HAMON TRAINING.
WE'LL JUST SEE ABOUT THAT.
♪
Erina: SO I SEE.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE SAFE,
AND MY GRANDSON, TOO.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'VE EVER BEEN HAPPIER.
( Speedwagon laughs )
( sighs )
JoJo: HEY,
IF YOU MENTION ONE WORD
ABOUT THOSE STUPID
POISON RINGS TO GRANNY,
I'LL BEAT YOU SENSELESS.
Speedwagon: IT WOULD DO NO GOOD
TO TELL HER ANYTHING.
( Speedwagon and Smokey sigh )
Lisa Lisa: NO SENSE
WASTING ANY MORE OF MY TIME.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY
FOR THE HELL CLIMB PILLAR!
Caesar: WAIT. SERIOUSLY?
JoJo: WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
Caesar: BUT‐‐BUT, COACH,
YOU KNOW THAT I HAVEN'T
EVEN MADE AN ATTEMPT
ON HELL CLIMB PILLAR, RIGHT?
DO YOU REALLY INTEND FOR US
TO START ON THIS?
SO MANY HAVE DIED
ON HELL CLIMB PILLAR.
I'VE HEARD COUNTLESS STORIES.
Lisa Lisa: STORIES THAT MAY
OR MAY NOT BE TRUE.
IF YOU FAIL,
YOU HAVE NO PLACE HERE.
JoJo: HELLO.
WOULD SOMEBODY CARE
TO CLUE ME IN
ON WHAT'S GOING ON?
THIS HELL PILLAR THING DOESN'T
REALLY LOOK ALL THAT TALL.
Lisa Lisa: WELL, FROM UP HERE,
IT'S REALLY MORE DEEP THAN TALL.
JoJo: HUH?
Caesar: COACH, WAIT!
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS!
( both yell )
( JoJo gasps )
( Caesar shuddering )
JoJo: WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
OIL.
THIS PILLAR IS COVERED
IN FLOWING OIL.
Lisa Lisa: IT'S 24 METERS
TO THE TOP OF THE PILLAR,
AND YOU MAY ONLY USE
YOUR HANDS TO CLIMB.
THERE IS NO OTHER WAY OUT.
IF YOU CAN'T FIND A WAY
TO CLIMB BACK,
YOU'LL DIE DOWN THERE.
JoJo: BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT ANYONE
COULD CLIMB UP THAT PILLAR.
♪
( waves crashing )
( Caesar breathing deeply )
Narrator: JOJO AND CAESAR
MUST NOW OVERCOME
THE MOST GRUELING
OF ALL HAMON ENDURANCE TESTS,
THE HELL CLIMB PILLAR.
Caesar: THIS IS REALLY BAD.
I CAN BARELY CLING
TO THE PILLAR,
AND MOVING MY FINGERS EVEN
A LITTLE BIT IS SO EXHAUSTING.
IF I WERE TO FALL NOW,
I WOULDN'T HAVE ANYTHING LEFT
TO START CLIMBING AGAIN.
BUT I CAN'T THINK
LIKE THAT RIGHT NOW.
OTHERWISE, JOJO AND I WILL
BOTH STARVE TO DEATH DOWN HERE.
( JoJo gurgles )
Caesar: JOJO! THE LONGER
YOU STAY IN THAT MUCK,
THE HARDER IT IS TO CLIMB OUT.
NOW FOCUS, AND‐‐
NO.
I MUST STAY FOCUSED ON MYSELF.
I CAN'T GET DISTRACTED,
NOT EVEN FOR A SECOND.
JoJo: THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
I JUST GOT HERE!
THAT SMUG WITCH
KNOWS I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO CLIMB THIS STUPID,
STUPID, STUPID, STUPID THING!
IT'S NOT FAIR!
JUST WHO THE HELL
DOES SHE THINK SHE IS, ANYWAY,
THROWING US DOWN THIS HOLE?
THERE'S NO WAY I COULD POSSIBLY
RESPECT HER AFTER THIS.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN PATIENT
WHEN IT COMES TO WOMEN,
BUT SHE'D BETTER START PRAYING
THAT I NEVER
MAKE IT OUT OF HERE ALIVE.
BLOODY HELL.
( chuckles )
SO THIS IDIOTIC PILLAR
CLAIMED THE LIVES
OF A LOT OF TRAINEES,
IS THAT RIGHT?
MAYBE THEY WERE
ALL JUST TOO DIMWITTED
TO COME UP WITH
A CREATIVE SOLUTION.
( gasps )
( yells )
Lisa Lisa:
USING ANYTHING BUT HAMON
IS AN INSULT TO THE PILLAR
AND YOUR TRAINING.
THE HELL CLIMB PILLAR
ONLY ACCEPTS HAMON.
IT REFUSES ANYTHING ELSE,
SO DON'T EVER FORGET THAT.
WAIT A SEC!
COME BACK, LISA LISA!
I MEAN, COACH! WAIT!
Y‐YOU WOULDN'T REALLY
LEAVE ME DOWN HERE TO ROT
JUST BECAUSE
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH POWER
TO CLIMB OUT OF HERE,
WOULD YOU?
I MEAN, IT'S MY FIRST DAY.
THIS IS JUST
SOME KIND OF TEST, RIGHT?
TO TEACH ME HUMILITY?
YOU'LL PULL ME OUT LATER,
RIGHT? RIGHT?!
( gasps )
HER EYES ARE LIKE ICE.
SHE REALLY MEANS IT.
SHE'S JUST GOING
TO LET ME DIE DOWN HERE.
CURSE HER. WHAT GIVES HER
THE RIGHT TO DO THIS?
THE FACT THAT SHE'S
SO DAMN BEAUTIFUL
JUST MAKES ME EVEN MORE FURIOUS
ABOUT THIS WHOLE THING!
♪
Narrator: 28 HOURS LATER,
CAESAR IS AT 15 METERS,
WHILE JOJO IS AT ZERO METERS.
THE RINGS WILL NOW DISSOLVE
IN 28 DAYS.
JoJo: I'M PRETTY SURE
WE'VE BEEN IN HERE OVERNIGHT,
AND CAESAR STILL HAS A LONG WAY
TO GO UP THAT PILLAR.
I SHOULD BE FOCUSING ON MYSELF,
BUT I CAN TELL
THAT HE'S REALLY STRUGGLING.
( gasps )
HIS FINGERS LOOK LIKE
THEY'RE ABOUT TO COME LOOSE.
IF‐‐IF HE LOSES THAT GRIP,
HE'S GOING TO COME SLIDING DOWN.
HIS HAMON LOOKS LIKE
IT'S ABOUT TO RUN OUT.
CAESAR, FOCUS!
( sighs )
( gasps ) HE LOOKS LIKE
HE'S ABOUT TO FALL AGAIN.
HE'S HANGING BY HIS FINGERTIPS.
CAESAR!
( gasps ) WAIT A SECOND.
IS THAT HOW HE'S BEEN CLIMBING
THIS ENTIRE TIME?
BY USING
JUST HIS FINGERTIPS LIKE THAT?
HE WASN'T
ABOUT TO FALL OFF AT ALL.
HE WAS JUST...
Caesar: THINK OF IT
LIKE USING A SQUIRT GUN
WITH ITS SMALLER HOLE...
JoJo: THAT'S‐‐THAT'S IT!
IT TOTALLY MAKES SENSE NOW.
( breathing deeply )
♪
CONSIDER
THIS HAMON MYSTERY SOLVED.
LET'S SEE HOW THIS WORKS.
I DID IT. IT'S WORKING.
MY HAMON IS STICKING
TO THE PILLAR.
ALL THIS TIME,
I HAD MY HANDS FLAT.
I WAS TRYING TO USE THEM
TO SUPPORT MY WEIGHT,
WHEN IN FACT,
IT'S THE OPPOSITE THAT WORKS.
FOCUSED HAMON CONCENTRATED
INTO THE FINGERTIPS
IS WHERE THE TRUE STRENGTH LIES.
WHAT A SIMPLE LITTLE TRICK.
I'VE GOT IT NOW.
ALL I HAVE TO DO FROM HERE ON UP
IS JUST CLIMB
AND PLOT MY REVENGE
ON THAT SO‐CALLED HAMON COACH.
( laughs )
Caesar: JOJO'S GOT IT.
GOOD FOR HIM.
Narrator: ANOTHER 24 HOURS
HAVE PASSED.
CAESAR IS NOW AT 18 METERS,
AND JOJO IS AT 16 METERS.
THE RINGS WILL DISSOLVE
IN EXACTLY 27 DAYS.
JoJo: OH, BOY.
NOW I CAN SEE WHY CAESAR
STARTED TO SLOW DOWN SO MUCH
ONCE HE GOT TO THIS POINT.
THE PILLAR BEGINS CURVING
OUTWARD HERE AS IT GOES UP.
THIS IS WHERE THINGS
ARE GOING TO GET TOUGH.
THE PILLAR IS AS UNFORGIVING
AS THAT DAMN LISA LISA.
CAESAR IS AT 19 METERS,
JOJO AT 18 METERS.
JoJo: OHH. IS THAT A‐‐
YES, IT IS. IT'S A CRACK,
AND IT SHOULD BE
JUST BIG ENOUGH FOR MY FINGERS.
THANK GOODNESS.
TIME FOR
A WELL‐EARNED BREAK HERE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE MY LUCK.
THINGS ARE FINALLY
STARTING TO LOOK UP FOR ME.
( gasps ) OH, NO.
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT FELT LIKE
SOME KIND OF SWITCH.
( rumbling )
Caesar: DID YOU FEEL THAT, JOJO?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
JoJo: WHAT THE‐‐OH, NO.
Lisa Lisa: THE HELL CLIMB PILLAR
ONLY ACCEPTS HAMON.
IT REFUSES ANYTHING ELSE.
Caesar: WATCH OUT!
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING!
JoJo: NOT GOOD. I MUST HAVE
TRIPPED SOME SORT OF BOOBY TRAP.
Caesar: THIS JUST WENT
FROM DIFFICULT TO IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW IN THE WORLD ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO SCALE THIS THING NOW?
Narrator: AN IMPENETRABLE SHEET
OF OIL SHOOTS OUT OF THE PILLAR
AT A DEADLY SPEED
NEAR THE 20‐METER MARK.
( Caesar gasps )
THAT STREAM
IS SO HIGHLY PRESSURIZED
THAT IT CAN CUT LIKE A RAZOR.
( JoJo gasps ) WHAT?
STOP LOOKING AT ME LIKE THAT.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
YOU CAN'T BE MAD AT ME.
( Caesar exhales )
( scoffs )
JoJo: LOOK, I'M SORRY, OKAY?
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO REST FOR A SECOND.
I DID WHAT ANY OTHER
SANE PERSON WOULD HAVE DONE.
WHATEVER MADMAN DESIGNED
THIS DIABOLICAL THING
SET THAT UP AS A TRAP.
Caesar: I WASN'T GIVING YOU
A LOOK OF BLAME, JOJO.
I WAS GIVING YOU
ONE OF CONCERN.
I'M NOT EVEN SURE
IF I CAN FOCUS MY HAMON
ENOUGH TO GET
THROUGH THAT OIL IN ONE PIECE.
THERE IS ONE WAY UP!
♪
JoJo: WHOA. WHAT THE...
HE'S STICKING TO THE PILLAR
WITH HIS FEET.
( Caesar breathes deeply )
JoJo: CAESAR!
Caesar: HAMON TO ATTRACT
AND REPEL.
MY HAMON IS NOW
FOCUSED THROUGH MY FEET
TO KEEP ME ON THE PILLAR
AND IN MY HANDS TO PROTECT ME
AS I BREAK THROUGH THE OIL.
I MUST STAY FOCUSED
TO CONTROL THE TWO OPPOSING
TYPES OF HAMON SIMULTANEOUSLY.
♪
I DID IT.
I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT JOJO ISN'T EVEN CLOSE
TO BEING ABLE TO CONTROL
TWO TYPES OF HAMON AT ONCE.
THERE'S NO WAY
HE CAN GET THROUGH THAT.
JoJo: THAT‐‐THAT WAS AMAZING.
I'M GLAD CAESAR WAS ABLE TO FIND
HIS WAY THROUGH THE OIL SOMEHOW,
BUT THERE'S NO WAY I CAN PULL
OFF A HAMON STUNT LIKE THAT.
♪
Narrator: NINE HOURS LATER...
( Caesar grunting )
Narrator: HE'S DONE IT.
CAESAR REACHES THE TOP
AFTER 61 HOURS.
( Caesar panting )
PLEASE, COACH.
JOJO CAN'T MAKE IT THROUGH THAT.
YOU'VE GOT TO TURN OFF THE OIL
FOR HIM.
THE MAN HAS NO PATIENCE AT ALL.
HE'LL UNDOUBTEDLY TRY
SOME STUPID DO‐OR‐DIE STUNT
ANY SECOND NOW, AND HE'LL FAIL.
( JoJo gasps )
WELL, I KNOW
THAT HANGING AROUND LIKE THIS
WON'T GET ME ANYWHERE.
Caesar: YOU'VE GOT
TO TURN THAT OIL OFF.
IF HE TRIES
TO BREAK THROUGH IT,
THE OIL WILL END UP
CUTTING HIM IN HALF.
AND EVEN IF HE'S
JUST BLASTED TO THE GROUND,
HE'LL END UP
STARVING TO DEATH DOWN THERE.
COACH, PLEASE!
JoJo: AH, TO HELL WITH IT!
I'LL MAKE IT OR DIE TRYING.
HERE GOES NOTHING!
Caesar: JOJO, DON'T!
JUST STAY RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE!
JoJo: I CAN USE
THE STRENGTH OF MY HAMON
TO GET ME OUT OF THIS, TOO.
‐ ( yells )
‐ ( Caesar gasps )
JOJO!
( gasps )
LOOK AT THAT.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
HE'S USING HIS HAMON
TO SLIDE ALONG THE PLANE
OF THE OIL SHEET.
THE OIL LOSES ITS SPEED
THE FARTHER IT SHOOTS OUT.
I'LL HAVE TO LAUNCH FROM HERE!
( Caesar gasps )
( JoJo yelling )
Caesar: HE ACTUALLY USED
THE MOMENTUM OF THE OIL
TO WHIP HIMSELF
UP AND OVER THE TOP OF IT.
HE DIDN'T FALL.
IN FACT, IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S MADE IT
UP A WHOLE THREE METERS.
Lisa Lisa:
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
ASCEND THE HELL CLIMB PILLAR
LIKE THAT BEFORE.
HE DID IT BY TURNING
HIS WEAKNESS INTO A STRENGTH.
THAT WAS QUITE CLEVER.
JoJo: I‐I MADE IT.
KIND OF, ANYWAY.
I'M ON THE WALL.
BUT IT'S NOT OVER YET.
THIS OVERHANG HERE IS EVEN WORSE
THAN THE ONE THAT WAS
ON THE PILLAR DOWN BELOW.
( grunting )
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING LEFT.
I'VE JUST GOT ONE MORE METER
TO GO, DAMN IT.
I‐I CAN'T CONTROL
MY BREATHING ANY LONGER.
I'M SLIPPING.
NO!
♪
C‐CAESAR.
Caesar: LET ME
SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT.
I WAS NOT MAD AT YOU
EARLIER, JOJO.
I'M SORRY.
FORGIVE ME, COACH,
BUT I JUST COULDN'T
LET JOJO GO DOWN LIKE THAT.
Lisa Lisa: I SUPPOSE
I UNDERSTAND, CAESAR,
ALTHOUGH I'M SURPRISED YOU
HAVE ANY STRENGTH LEFT YOURSELF.
( Caesar gasps )
OH, I FORGOT.
JoJo: I COULD REALLY USE
YOUR OTHER ARM HERE.
DON'T LET ME GO! CAESAR!
Narrator: 10 SECONDS LATER
AND AFTER SAYING,
"DON'T LET ME GO,"
ANOTHER 13 TIMES,
JOJO REACHES THE TOP.
( gloves creaking )
( JoJo laughs )
HELLO AGAIN, COACH.
I BET YOU THOUGHT
I WAS DONE FOR, HUH?
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT WHILE I WAS CLINGING
TO THAT PILLAR FOR DEAR LIFE,
I HAD TIME TO THINK TO MYSELF,
"HOW SHOULD I EXACT MY REVENGE
UPON THAT WITCH?!
"SHOULD I CHALLENGE HER
TO A DUEL?
OR MAYBE I SHOULD JUST SQUEEZE
HER NOSE UNTIL SHE CRIES."
Caesar: THAT'S INTERESTING.
I DIDN'T THINK JOJO
WOULD BE THE TYPE
THAT WOULD HOLD
A GRUDGE LIKE THAT.
JoJo: SO WHICH
WILL IT BE, COACH?
EH?
( gasps ) I‐I'M DOING IT.
I'M REALLY DOING IT.
I'M HOLDING THE WATER
IN THE CUP
WHEN IT'S UPSIDE DOWN.
Caesar: THAT'S GREAT.
IN ONLY THREE EXCRUCIATING DAYS,
HE'S IMPROVED
HIS HAMON CONTROL.
JOJO'S INHERENT TALENT
IS INCREDIBLE,
BUT COACH LISA LISA'S
HAMON TRAINING IS EVEN MORE SO.
JoJo: FORGIVE ME, COACH.
PLEASE, I'LL DO
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE ME MORE
TRAINING, I BEG YOU. PLEASE.
YOU'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
I'LL OVERCOME ANYTHING.
Caesar: WELL,
THAT WAS PRETTY QUICK.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D BE ABLE
TO HOLD A GRUDGE FOR VERY LONG.
Lisa Lisa:
OH, DON'T WORRY, JOJO.
I'VE GOT PLENTY MORE FOR YOU.
I WILL TRAIN YOU
INTO THE GROUND.
JoJo: THANK YOU, COACH.
Lisa Lisa:
YOUR NEXT THREE WEEKS HERE
ARE GOING TO MAKE THE HELL CLIMB
PILLAR LOOK LIKE A CAKEWALK.
JoJo: HUH?
WHO THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU ARE,
SNEAKING UP ON ME LIKE THAT?
( Caesar gasps )
♪
JoJo: WHOA. WHO ARE THESE GUYS?
Caesar: HE'S MADE THE WATER
MOVE LIKE PUDDING.
Lisa Lisa:
I WOULD LIKE FOR YOU TO MEET
TWO OF MY FINEST SERVANTS.
THESE MEN WILL BE
YOUR NEW INSTRUCTORS.
SAY HELLO TO MESHINA AND LOGGS.
Caesar: I‐I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE
HOW TO DO THAT.
Loggs: WOULD YOU
LIKE TO LEARN, THEN?
Caesar: EH?
Loggs: DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME ASK
IF YOU WANTED TO LEARN
HOW TO DO THIS?
Caesar: YES, OF COURSE I DID.
LEARNING FROM YOU
WOULD BE AN HONOR.
Loggs: WELL, FINE THEN.
COME CLOSER, TAKE A LOOK,
AND I'LL SHOW YOU
WHAT'S GOING ON.
‐ ( Caesar gasps )
‐ JoJo: HUH?
( both yelp )
( Meshina and Loggs laughing )
Loggs: WHY DO YOU CHUMPS
WANT HAMON TRAINING?
Meshina: NO MATTER.
FROM HERE ON OUT, WE'RE GONNA...
Meshina and Loggs:
FORGE YOU INTO REAL MEN!
♪
Meshina: STRENGTHEN YOUR BREATH.
HOW CAN YOUR MUSCLES BE STRONG
IF WHAT SUPPORTS THEM
IS WEAK AS A BUTTERFLY?
YOU MUST BE ABLE
TO TAKE 10 FULL BREATHS
IN A SINGLE SECOND.
JoJo: UGH! THIS SUCKS!
Loggs: YOU WILL INHALE
FOR 10 MINUTES
AND THEN EXHALE FOR 10 MINUTES.
THE MASK DOESN'T
COME OFF UNTIL THEN.
( JoJo groans ) REALLY?
OHH! YOU GUYS ARE INSANE.
SEVEN DAYS REMAIN
UNTIL THE RINGS DISSOLVE.
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ WITH YOU
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
( vocalizing )
♪
Lisa Lisa:
I'M AFRAID IT'S NECESSARY
‐ FOR A FINAL EXAMINATION
‐ Kars: THE SOLUTION
‐ IS FINDING MORE POWER.
‐ Caesar: DEEP DOWN,
‐ HE'S WORTH HAVING AS A FRIEND.
‐ JoJo: HORRIBLE. UNNATURAL!
Esidisi: I JUST CAN'T TAKE IT!
( sobs )