♪
( woman screams )
Narrator: SEVEN YEARS LATER,
IN 1888...
JACK THE RIPPER STALKED
THE STREETS OF LONDON,
MURDERING WOMEN IN THE NIGHT
AND HOLDING THE ENTIRE CITY
IN HIS THRALL.
HOWEVER, HE WAS NOTHING
COMPARED TO THE HORROR
THAT THE FEUD
BETWEEN JOJO AND DIO
WOULD UNLEASH UPON THE WORLD.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Commentator: INTERCEPTION!
THE BALL IS PLUCKED
OUT OF THE AIR
BY OUR HERO, JONATHAN JOESTAR!
JOESTAR, A GENTLE GIANT
AT 195 CENTIMETERS,
SPRINTS FOR THE TRY ZONE
WITH A SPIRITED ROAR!
CAN HE WIN THIS, THE LAST GAME
OF HIS UNIVERSITY CAREER?
( player yells )
Commentator:
HE'S TACKLED FROM BEHIND!
WAIT! HE'S STILL STANDING TALL.
( JoJo chuckles )
Commentator: TWO MORE FLY IN.
IT'S THREE ON ONE OUT THERE!
( JoJo grunting )
Player #2: HUH?
Player #3: EH?
Commentator: INCREDIBLE!
HE'S STILL MAKING
FOR THE TRY LINE,
UNDAUNTED BY THE MEN
WHO DOG HIS STEPS.
WHAT POWER. WHAT DETERMINATION.
HE'S HERCULES REBORN.
‐ ( player #4 yells )
‐ Commentator: ANOTHER TACKLE!
OH, THE WEIGHT'S
TOO MUCH FOR HIM!
( JoJo grunts )
( yells )
Commentator:
HE FLINGS IT AWAY, AND...
YES! THERE'S THE CATCH.
THE BALL LANDS SAFE
IN THE HANDS OF DIO BRANDO.
IT'S STILL ANYONE'S GAME!
( players yell )
( both grunt )
Commentator: CAN HE MAKE IT?
HE DODGES ONE AND ANOTHER!
HE'S DONE IT!
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
BETWEEN DIO AND THE TRY LINE,
AND STILL HE GIVES IT HIS ALL.
YES!
( crowd cheering )
Commentator: THEY DID IT!
ON THE LAST PLAY,
THEY SNATCHED VICTORY
OUT OF THE JAWS OF DEFEAT.
WHAT TEAMWORK.
WHEN JOJO AND DIO WORK TOGETHER,
THERE'S NOTHING THEY CAN'T DO.
Dio: HELL OF A PASS, JOJO.
JoJo: ALL FOR NAUGHT IF YOU
HADN'T RUN IT IN LIKE YOU DID.
Dio: WATCHING YOU
DRAG THOSE DEFENDERS,
I COULDN'T JUST LET YOU DOWN.
Commentator:
HAVING FINISHED HIS STUDIES,
DIO IS SET TO GRADUATE
WITH TOP MARKS IN LAW.
JOJO, MEANWHILE,
HAS SET THE FACULTY AFIRE
WITH HIS BOLD THESIS
ON ARCHEOLOGY.
ON AND OFF THE FIELD,
THESE TWO YOUNG MEN ARE GIANTS.
THEY'RE THE PRIDE
OF OUR SCHOOL.
Dio: JOJO, I THINK
WE SHOULD TELL OUR FATHER
ABOUT THIS VICTORY OF OURS
AT ONCE.
( JoJo grunts )
IT'S BEEN SEVEN YEARS NOW
SINCE MY FATHER
WELCOMED DIO INTO OUR HOME,
SEVEN LONG YEARS.
I SMILE AND TREAT HIM
AS A BROTHER,
BUT IN MY HEART, NOTHING COULD
BE FURTHER FROM THE TRUTH.
HE'S NOTHING IF NOT AFFABLE
AND SMART AS A WHIP...
BUT I JUST CAN'T FORGIVE HIM
FOR HIS EARLY VILLAINIES.
Reporter: DIO,
MIGHTN'T YOU GIVE US A QUOTE
ABOUT YOUR FRIENDSHIP WITH JOJO?
YOU SEEM QUITE CLOSE.
Dio: WRITE ABOUT THE TEAM,
ALL OF US.
Man: COME ON.
TELL US HOW CLOSE YOU ARE.
Dio: HMM. SHOULD I?
HEH.
FRIENDSHIP, HUH?
THE TRUTH IS I DESPISE
THIS GRINNING IMBECILE.
I'VE SPENT SEVEN YEARS
MAKING NICE
TO THAT JOESTAR BRAT,
BUT NOW THAT I AM OF AGE,
I SHALL BRING
MY PLANS TO FRUITION.
AT LONG LAST, THE JOESTAR
FORTUNE WILL BE MINE,
AND DEVIL TAKE
ANYONE WHO TRIES TO STOP ME.
( man coughing )
Dio: FATHER,
HOW ARE YOU FEELING TODAY?
George: BUT FOR THIS COUGH,
MUCH IMPROVED OVER YESTERDAY.
( coughs )
THE DOCTORS SAY
I SHOULD BE IN THE HOSPITAL.
Dio: WHY? I FEAR
IT WOULD DO YOU NO GOOD.
HOSPITALS ONLY CARE
ABOUT PROFIT.
THEY'D MEASURE YOU FOR A SHROUD
ERE THEY SAW YOU CURED.
George: HMM.
THEN HERE I SHALL REMAIN.
THE COMFORTS OF HOME
ARE CURATIVE, LIKE AS NOT.
MY CHEST DOESN'T PAIN ME SO,
AND THE SWELLING HAS GONE DOWN.
I'M ON THE MEND.
‐ ( coughs )
‐ JoJo: IT WAS JUST A COLD.
WHY HAS IT WORSENED SO?
George: I HEARD TELL
OF YOUR VICTORY.
STUNNING BIT OF TEAMWORK.
JoJo: SOMEONE
TOLD YOU ABOUT IT?
George: I GOT WORD STRAIGHTAWAY
FROM AN OLD COLLEGE CHUM.
Dio: WHOEVER HE IS, HE'S FAST.
I'M GLAD HE WASN'T
ON OUR OPPONENTS' TEAM,
OR WE COULD HAVE LOST.
( both laughing )
George: I'M PROUD OF YOU, LADS.
YOU BOTH TURNED OUT SO WELL.
PROVIDENCE IS TOO KIND.
DIO, I'M SO GLAD YOU'VE THRIVED.
PURSUE YOUR AMBITIONS,
WHATEVER THEY MAY BE.
I WILL LEND YOU AID
IN ANY WAY I CAN, MY SON.
Dio: YOU RESCUED ME
FROM CALAMITY.
ALREADY MY DEBT IS MORE
THAN I CAN EVER REPAY.
YOU DO ME TOO MUCH HONOR.
♪
JoJo: THIS SECRET IS MINE ALONE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE FOR WHAT PURPOSE
THIS MASK MAY HAVE
BEEN FASHIONED OR BY WHOM,
BUT IT BELONGED TO MY MOTHER,
AND SO HAVING IT NEAR
IS A COMFORT,
STRANGE AS THAT MAY SEEM.
WHEN I FINALLY OUTWIT
THIS SPHINX OF A MASK,
IT WILL BE THE TALK
OF THE ARCHEOLOGICAL WORLD.
MY GOODNESS!
Butler: MANY THANKS TO YOU,
MASTER DIO.
THE YEARS BETRAY ME.
CLIMBING THE STAIRS IS
MUCH HARDER THAN IT WAS BEFORE.
JoJo: THIS LETTER,
HAVING READ IT,
ALL HAS BEEN MADE CLEAR.
DIO...
I THINK HE'S...
( Dio chuckles )
♪
JoJo: DIO!
WAIT. THAT'S‐‐
THAT'S FATHER'S MEDICINE.
Dio: HE'S DUE
FOR HIS NEXT DOSAGE.
JoJo: ALL THIS TIME,
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S BEEN BRINGING IT TO HIM.
Dio: YES. WHAT OF IT?
JoJo: THIS LETTER,
YOUR FATHER SENT IT TO MINE.
GUESS WHAT IT SAYS.
"YOUR LORDSHIP,
SICKNESS HAS LAID ME RIGHT LOW.
"IT'S THE END OF ME,
WHATEVER IT IS.
"MY CHEST HURTS,
"MY FINGERS'RE ALL SWOLE UP,
AND I CAN'T BREATHE,
BUT FOR ALL THIS COUGHING."
THOSE ARE THE SAME SYMPTOMS
AS FATHER'S, BLOW FOR BLOW!
NO WAY IS THIS
MERE COINCIDENCE.
DIO!
Dio: WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO SAY, JOJO?
JoJo: I'M HAVING A DOCTOR
LOOK AT THIS POWDER.
Dio: JOJO, IF YOU THINK
I WOULD POISON FATHER,
THEN FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
YOU AND I...
ARE FRIENDS NO MORE!
( JoJo gasping )
TRY AS I MIGHT,
I CAN'T LOOK DIO IN THE EYE.
IT'S BECAUSE I LACK PROOF.
ALL I HAVE TO GO ON
ARE MY SUSPICIONS.
Dio: NOW, THEN, IF YOU PUT
THAT MEDICINE BACK ON THE TRAY,
I'LL BE WILLING TO FORGET
ABOUT YOUR LAPSE IN JUDGMENT.
JoJo: DIO,
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
YOU'RE GOING TO CONVINCE ME.
SWEAR TO ME THAT
THE CONTENTS OF THIS ARE SAFE.
DO IT IN DARIO'S NAME.
SWEAR TO ME ON DARIO'S HONOR
AS A GENTLEMAN.
DO THAT, AND I'LL NEVER
BRING UP THIS MOMENT AGAIN.
( Dio gasps )
JoJo: IF MY HUNCH PROVES TRUE,
HIS FATHER'S HONOR
IS THE ONE LIE
THAT WILL CATCH IN HIS THROAT.
SAY IT!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
Dio: I S‐SWEAR...
HOW CAN I SWEAR
ON THE HONOR OF A MAN
WHO DIDN'T HAVE ANY?!
HE DESERVED TO DIE!
HOW'S THAT
FOR THE TRUTH, JOJO?!
JoJo: YOU JUST GAVE ME
ALL THE PROOF I NEEDED, DIO.
AT HEARING HIS NAME,
YOU LASHED OUT.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HE COULD HAVE DONE
THAT MOVED YOU
TO SUCH MURDEROUS RAGE,
BUT MURDER HIM, YOU SURELY DID.
( Dio gasping )
YOU HURT FATHER.
NEVER AGAIN, DIO.
( Dio groans )
DAMN YOUR EYES.
JoJo: OF COURSE.
YOU'VE BEEN PLANNING
TO MURDER HIM FOR YEARS NOW.
I KNEW IT. I KNEW THAT YOU
WERE PLAYING FALSE WITH US.
BUT NOW YOUR VILLAINY IS OVER.
ONCE I'VE LEARNED WHAT THIS IS,
I'M TAKING IT
TO THE POLICE STRAIGHTAWAY.
( Dio sputters )
DAMN IT.
THEIR FORTUNE
WAS WITHIN MY GRASP.
WAS IT FATE THAT JOJO
FOUND OUT WHEN HE DID?
NO. IT WAS THAT LETTER.
HE VEXES ME EVEN NOW.
Dario: YOU'RE WEAK,
JUST LIKE YOUR MOTHER!
Dio: HE DROVE HER
TO AN EARLY GRAVE.
KNOWING THAT CUR'S BLOOD
FLOWS THROUGH MY VEINS,
IT'S ENOUGH TO DRIVE ME MAD!
♪
SIR JOESTAR LIVES FOR NOW.
JoJo: I'LL BE BACK FROM LONDON
IN A FEW DAYS, FATHER.
'TIL THEN, ACCEPT MEDICINE ONLY
FROM THE HANDS OF THESE DOCTORS
AND NO ONE ELSE.
Butler: MASTER JOJO SAID HE
DOESN'T WANT ME TO BRING IT UP?
George: YES. WE WILL DO
AS JOJO HAS INSTRUCTED US.
HIS REASONS ARE A MYSTERY TO ME,
BUT I TRUST THE BOY
WITH MY LIFE. ( coughs )
JoJo: THANK YOU, FATHER.
HIS ILLNESS IS GETTING WORSE.
( horses galloping )
IF IT IS A POISON,
HE MAY NEED AN ANTIDOTE.
♪
Dio: WHATEVER YOU MAY LEARN
IN LONDON ABOUT THE POISON,
I'LL SEE YOU TAKE
THE TRUTH OF IT TO YOUR GRAVE.
YOUR DEATH WILL BE
THE PERFECT CRIME.
SEVEN YEARS AGO,
THIS MASK REACTED TO MY BLOOD.
THE SPIKES HIDDEN WITHIN WILL
MAKE SHORT WORK OF JOJO'S BRAIN.
HIS INJURIES WILL BE SO UNIQUE,
THERE'LL BE NOTHING AT ALL
TO TIE IT BACK TO ME.
JOJO, YOUR CURIOSITY
WILL LEAD TO YOUR DESTRUCTION.
‐ Driver: WHOA. WHOA.
‐ ( horses neigh )
JoJo: THE UNIVERSITY COULDN'T
IDENTIFY THE SO‐CALLED MEDICINE,
THOUGH THEY DID SPECULATE
THAT IT WAS A COMPOUND
FROM THE ORIENT.
THEREFORE...
Driver: YOUNG MASTER,
THAT STRETCH OF ROAD THERE
IS OGRE STREET,
THE MOST DANGEROUS ALLEYWAY
IN ALL OF LONDON.
JoJo: YES, I KNOW,
BUT THIS IS THE ONE PLACE
I WILL BE ABLE TO FIND
WHAT I CAME FOR.
YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO LEAVE.
Driver: HMM?
JoJo: DIO GREW UP IN LONDON.
WHERE ELSE IN ENGLAND COULD HE
HAVE ACQUIRED SUCH A TOXIN?
I SHALL HAVE MY EVIDENCE...
AND FATHER'S ANTIDOTE.
♪
ANOTHER DEAD END.
( cat screeches )
( JoJo gasps ) THAT CAT...
‐ IT WAS EATING A PUPPY.
‐ ( man whistles )
♪
Man: YOU DO THE HONORS, TATTOO.
Tattoo: RIGHT!
Man: USE THAT SHIV OF YOURS
TO SLICE HIM OPEN.
I WANT HIS GUTS FOR GARTERS!
JoJo: OGRE STREET.
IT IS APTLY NAMED.
( Tattoo screams )
( chuckles )
CHECK OUT THIS IDIOT!
HE GRABBED MY BLADE!
IN ALL MY DAYS,
I'VE NEVER SEEN THE LIKE.
HA HA HA! STUCK, AIN'T YA?
ONE QUICK YANK OF THE KNIFE,
AND THEY'LL BE
PICKING YOUR FINGERS
OUT OF THE SNOW FOR A FORTNIGHT.
JoJo: TRY IT, THEN.
THE MOMENT YOU PULL,
MY FOOT WILL KICK OUT
AT YOUR GROIN
WITH ALL THE FORCE
OF A SLEDGEHAMMER.
I'M WILLING TO SEE
OUR TRANSACTION THROUGH.
ARE YOU, SIRRAH?
I'M FIGHTING
TO PROTECT MY FAMILY
FROM THOSE WHO WISH IT HARM.
I DOUBT VERY MUCH THAT
YOUR RESOLVE IS EQUAL TO MINE.
( man #2 yells )
JoJo: THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH.
NOW TELL ME, ONE OF YOU,
WHERE CAN I FIND
AN ASIAN APOTHECARY?
Man #1: TOUGH TALK.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING
TO LOSE BODY PARTS,
DO STICK AROUND.
OBSERVE.
( metal clinks )
( JoJo gasps )
Man #1: I'LL MINCE YA
RIGHT FINELY
WITH A TIP OF THE HAT.
AND NOW, WE DANCE.
JoJo: I HAVE TO FIND
THAT APOTHECARY,
NO MATTER THE COST.
Man #1: DON'T TELL ME
THIS HERE'S
YOUR FIRST PROPER DUST‐UP.
IF YOU MEAN TO BLOCK LIKE THAT,
IT'LL BE YOUR LAST ONE, TOO.
HA HA!
CUT YA STRAIGHT TO THE BONE,
LOOKS LIKE.
GRANTED, I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D
HOOF THE SHIV AT ME LIKE THAT,
BUT MY CHAPEAU
STILL HIT ITS MARK.
♪
NOW I KNOW WHY HE WEREN'T
DEFENDING HIMSELF BETTER.
FINGERS, HANDS, LEGS,
HE DON'T CARE
ONE WHIT WHAT HE LOSES.
IT'S AS IF HIS RESOLVE
RUNS DEEPER THAN PAIN OR FEAR.
I TOOK THE LAD FOR AN EASY MARK.
GUESS I'VE BEEN RIGHT DISABUSED
OF THAT NOTION.
♪
( men murmuring, chuckling )
Dio: WHAT? JOJO WENT
TO OGRE STREET ON HIS OWN?
Driver: I TOLD HIM
IT WAS PERILOUS.
Dio: KEEP THIS TO YOURSELF.
SIR JOESTAR IS STILL UNWELL.
Driver: YES, SIR.
Dio: I GUESS I WON'T NEED
TO USE THE MASK AFTER ALL.
THERE, ALONE?
HIS FATE IS SEALED.
( men laughing )
Man #1: THAT'S ENOUGH, LADS!
I WON'T LET A SINGLE ONE OF YA
LAY A FINGER
ON THAT GENTLEMAN THERE.
( JoJo gasps )
BUT WHY?
Man #1: TELL ME SOMETHING.
STRONG AS A BULL, YOU ARE.
IT'S PLAIN TO SEE.
YOU COULDA STOVE MY HEAD IN
WITH THAT FOOT OF YOURS,
BUT YOU WENT EASY ON ME,
DIDN'T YOU?
( men gasp )
JoJo: I CAME HERE
FOR THE SAKE OF MY FATHER.
YOU HAVE A FAMILY,
PEOPLE WHO EXPECT YOU TO RETURN
FROM THIS DARK BUSINESS.
IT IS NOT MY PLACE
TO CAUSE THEM GRIEF.
Man #1: HE MEANS IT, DON'T HE?
HOW'D THIS FELLA
SURVIVE SO LONG?
WAIT.
HE SPARED MY MATES' LIVES,
JUST LIKE HE DID MINE.
I LIKE THE CUT OF HIS JIB.
SURE, HE'S NA ÏVE,
BUT HE'S A GENTLEMAN
THROUGH AN' THROUGH, THIS ONE.
I WANNA KNOW THE NAME
OF HIM WHO SPARED ME.
JoJo: JONATHAN JOESTAR.
Man #1: WELL, PLEASED
TO MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
IF IT'S ASIAN CONCOCTIONS
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR,
MIND YOUR BACK.
THAT DRUGGIST
IS ONE SLY CUSTOMER.
Doctor: SIR JOESTAR,
JOJO'S BEEN GONE THREE DAYS.
George: WHATEVER HIS ERRAND,
HE'LL ACCOMPLISH IT.
Doctor: HEH. WHERE HAVE
THE YEARS GONE, I WONDER?
HE'S GROWN INTO A FINE MAN.
George: I CANNOT HELP BUT WONDER
IF I WAS TOO HARD
ON THE BOY GROWING UP.
( cat hisses )
( Dio groans )
I'M SURE JOJO'S LAYING DEAD
IN SOME ALLEY BY NOW.
DID HE FIND THE APOTHECARY?
LOOK AT ME. SWILLING IT DOWN.
NOTHING BUT A DRUNKEN FOOL,
JUST LIKE MY BASTARD FATHER.
DAMN IT!
( man laughs )
WATCH YOURSELF!
OR HAVE YOU NO RESPECT
FOR YOUR ELDERS, BOY?
LOOK AT THE BABY
TODDLING AROUND PAST BEDTIME,
SUCKING ON A BOTTLE
LIKE IT WAS HIS MOTHER'S TEAT.
( man #2 laughs )
LOOK AT THE MAN
WHEN HE'S TALKING.
DIDN'T YOUR OLD MAN
TEACH YOU RIGHT?
‐ ( man #1 wails )
‐ Man #2: MY GOD.
JUST FOR THAT, I'M GONNA
TAKE YOUR FACE CLEAN OFF YA.
Dio: OH. YOUR THREAT
HAS ME QUAKING IN MY BOOTS,
YOU OLD GUTTERSNIPE.
HOW WILL I ESCAPE
THIS MOMENT OF MORTAL PERIL?
HOW ABOUT...
WE USE THIS?
IT'S MEANT FOR JOJO,
BUT YOU'LL MAKE
A FINE GUINEA PIG.
Man #2: JUST DIE ALREADY!
EH?
Dio: LET'S SEE WHAT YOU CAN DO!
( man #1 gasping )
( Dio gasps )
W‐WHAT IS THAT LIGHT?
ALL OF THAT SPECTACLE
FOR NOTHING?
USELESS.
( spits )
THAT WAS BORING.
I EXPECTED MORE FROM YOU, MASK.
( wipes hat )
♪
( gasps )
IMPOSSIBLE.
HE'S ALIVE.
THAT FACE. THOSE TEETH.
‐ ( creature hisses )
‐ Dio: NO!
( creature shrieks )
Dio: WHAT INCREDIBLE STRENGTH.
( groans )
EVEN NOW, HE ADVANCES.
BUT HIS HAND...
DOES THE PAIN MEAN NOTHING?
HE SHATTERED MY SHOULDER
WITH BUT A GLANCING BLOW.
THE RIVER. I MUST JUMP IN.
( groans )
( blood flowing )
Creature: IT'S ODD.
I WAS DRINKING
THROUGH THE NIGHT,
BUT SUDDENLY
I GOT SUCH A BRUTAL THIRST.
Dio: MY BLOOD, HE'S DRAINING IT.
WHAT THE...
SO THIS IS
THE SECRET OF THE MASK.
I'M DYING.
( screams )
NO! I HAD SUCH PLANS!
MUST MY LAST SIGHT ON EARTH
BE THIS DAMNABLE SUNRISE?!
( creature screams )
Dio: THE SUN DESTROYED HIM.
♪
( thunder rumbling )
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF THIS?
WHY'S IT SO BLOODY DARK?
( match strikes )
JOJO.
JoJo: YOU'RE A POISONER,
DIO BRANDO.
I HAVE ALL THE PROOF
I REQUIRE AND THEN SOME.
( Dio gasps )
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Dio: JOJO, I'VE BEEN A DEVIL,
BUT GRANT ME THIS ONE WISH.
Man: THIS FELLOW REEKS
OF BRIMSTONE AND BLOOD.
Dio: YOU SEE, I AM ABOUT
TO BECOME SO MUCH MORE!
JoJo: DIO!