JoJo: HEY, RIFLE HEADS,
WHAT'S A GUY GOTTA DO
TO GET A LITTLE FOOD IN HERE?
KARS!
Kars: THIS MAN'S MECHANICAL.
JoJo: YOU'RE VON STROHEIM!
DOUBLE SHOCK!
THIS IS SPOOKIER
THAN MEETING A GHOST
IN A DARK CEMETERY
AFTER MIDNIGHT.
KARS...
AND VON STROHEIM,
WHO I COULD HAVE SWORN
WAS BLOWN INTO LITTLE,
TINY BITS BACK IN MEXICO,
THEY'RE BOTH STANDING
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
KARS,
AND VON STROHEIM IS HERE, TOO.
HIS HAND LOOKS LIKE
IT'S MADE OF METAL,
AND HIS FACE IS WRAPPED
IN SOME STRANGE MACHINERY.
THE GERMANS
MUST HAVE BEEN HIDING THIS.
WHAT INCREDIBLE
MEDICAL TECHNOLOGY.
COULD IT BE
FOR SOME KIND OF MILITARY USE?
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT SAVED YOUR
MISERABLE LIFE, VON STROHEIM.
Von Stroheim: JOJO, AS YOU
CAN SEE, I'M BACK FROM HELL.
( JoJo groans )
SHOULD I BE HAPPY ABOUT IT?
WHEN YOU GET DOWN TO IT,
HE'S NOT EXACTLY A BAD GUY,
EXCEPT FOR THE FACT
THAT HE'S A DAMN GERMAN SOLDIER.
AND I DON'T LIKE
THE WAY HE STRUTS AROUND
LIKE HE'S BETTER
THAN EVERYONE ELSE.
STILL, I AM A BIT HAPPY.
Von Stroheim: WHY DON'T YOU
MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME
ON THE SOFA UND WATCH ME
WHILE I DO MY WORK?
( JoJo gasps )
H‐HE'S GLARING AT ME.
HE KNOWS THAT I'M THE ONE
WHO KILLED ESIDISI,
AND HE HATES ME FOR IT.
EVEN SO...
KARS! DO YOU THINK
I'M GONNA JUST SIT HERE
AND LET YOU
TRY AND PSYCHE ME OUT?!
Kars: JOJO, ONCE I'M FINISHED
SECURING THE STONE,
I'M GOING TO PUT AN END YOU.
IT'S TOO BAD WAMUU
IS STILL OFF WORKING IN GREECE.
I CAN'T ALLOW A HAMON USER
WHO WAS ABLE TO BEAT ESIDISI
TO REMAIN ALIVE.
JoJo: TELL ME SOMETHING, KARS.
DO YOU SPEAK AS A WARRIOR,
OR ARE YOU AFTER SOMETHING ELSE,
LIKE REVENGE?
Von Stroheim: PAY ATTENTION.
YOU'RE FIGHTING ME.
I'M THE ONE WHO IS GOING
TO BE YOUR FINAL OPPONENT.
Kars: NO MACHINE CAN STOP ME.
Von Stroheim: IS THAT RIGHT?
( JoJo gasps )
ARMS OF FLESH AND BLOOD
CAN'T BEND LIKE THAT,
WHICH MEANS THEY ARE MECHANICAL.
( Kars grunts )
Von Stroheim: NOW FOR THE FUN.
JoJo: WAIT. HE'S‐‐
Narrator: HIS FINGERS SQUEEZE
AT 1,950 KILOGRAMS
PER CENTIMETER SQUARED,
ALMOST TWICE
SANTVIENTO'S STRENGTH
Von Stroheim: YOU UTTER FOOL!
GERMAN SCIENCE
IS THE FINEST IN THE WORLD!
THESE ARMS
HAVE SUCH GREAT POWER!
THEY WERE CONSTRUCTED BASED
ON THE ABILITIES OF SANTVIENTO!
‐ ( fingers whirring )
‐ UND SO, KARS...
WE CALCULATED EXACTLY
WHAT WE NEED TO DO TO YOU
IN ORDER TO ELIMINATE YOUR POWER
UND LEAVE YOU
IN DESPERATE AGONY.
I'M GOING TO PLUCK YOU
LIKE A CHICKEN, BIT BY BIT,
UND TAKE YOU APART
ONE SQUARE CENTIMETER AT A TIME.
HEY, JOJO...
JoJo: YOW! HEY.
Von Stroheim:
DON'T YOU DARE EVEN THINK
ABOUT FEELING SORRY FOR ME.
MY PROUD NEW FORM
IS THE VERY EMBODIMENT
OF THE ULTIMATE PEAK OF GERMAN
SCIENCE UND ENGINEERING!
YOU SEE, I'M NOT MERELY HUMAN.
I'M MORE!
TAKE THIS, KARS.
MY MACHINE GUN CAN FIRE
600 ROUNDS PER MINUTE
UND SHRED THROUGH ARMOR PLATING
LIKE IT WAS MADE OF PAPER.
IT'LL WHITTLE YOU DOWN INTO
TINY PIECES IN NO TIME AT ALL.
JoJo:
HIS BODY'S MECHANICAL, TOO?
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
...THE HELL WAS THAT?
Caesar: IT CAME FROM DOWNSTAIRS.
( Kars groaning )
I SWEAR THE STONE
WILL BE MINE TODAY.
ATTEMPTING TO GET IT
COST ESIDISI HIS LIFE.
I REFUSE TO ALLOW
HIS ULTIMATE SACRIFICE
TO HAVE BEEN IN VAIN.
‐ ( Von Stroheim gasps )
‐ JoJo: THAT LIGHT.
THE BLADE COMING
OUT OF HIS ARM IS GLOWING.
Kars: I CAN CONTROL LIGHT.
BEHOLD BRILLIANT BONE BLADE.
♪
( Von Stroheim gasps )
IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT BLADE IS
HARDENED BONE UND SKIN,
NOT WEAPONS‐GRADE FORGED STEEL.
IT SHOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO DEFLECT BULLETS LIKE THAT
LET ALONE SLICE THEM
IN HALF IN MIDAIR.
JoJo: HIS BLADE IS AMAZING,
BUT WHY IS IT GLOWING LIKE THAT?
Von Stroheim: HERE HE COMES.
HERE HE COMES.
HERE HE COMES. HERE HE COMES.
I‐‐I KNOW THAT SOUND.
Narrator:
UPON SEEING THE BLADE UP CLOSE,
VON STROHEIM WAS ABLE
TO UNDERSTAND ITS SECRET.
IT DIDN'T HAVE A SIMPLE EDGE.
RATHER, IT HAD A ROTATING BLADE
MOVING AT HIGH SPEED.
TINY, RAZOR‐SHARP CLAWS
SLID QUIETLY
ALONG THE OUTER EDGE
OF THE BLADE,
READY TO SHRED
ANYTHING IN ITS PATH.
EACH CLAW WAS FLAWLESSLY
POLISHED TO A MIRRORLIKE FINISH
AND REFRACTED
THE FAINTEST LIGHT,
MAKING THE BLADE LOOK AS THOUGH
IT WERE GLOWING FROM WITHIN.
Von Stroheim:
W‐WE CAN'T WIN THIS,
AT LEAST NOT WITH MY WEAPONS
OR ANY MODERN TECHNOLOGY
THAT I KNOW OF.
WE CAN'T DEFEAT HIM.
Kars: AND WHAT WAS SANTVIENTO?
NOTHING BUT A WEAK CHILD,
A WELL TRAINED GUARD DOG.
HE COULDN'T EVEN COMPARE TO US.
NOW I'LL TAKE THAT STONE.
JoJo: KARS. WHAT THE HELL?
THAT ICE‐COLD SHEEN
ACROSS HIS FACE.
A BLADE THAT CAN CUT BULLETS
IN MIDAIR.
THERE'S NO WAY
I COULD EVER BLOCK THAT THING
WITH ONLY MY BARE HANDS.
EVEN IF I COULD CONCENTRATE ALL
OF MY HAMON INTO A SINGLE BLOW,
THAT BLADE WOULD STILL
SLICE RIGHT THROUGH ME.
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
I WANT TO RUN AWAY FROM HERE.
HE'S WAY TOO DANGEROUS
TO TAKE ON DIRECTLY.
I CAN'T THINK OF ANY WAY
TO GET AROUND THAT BLADE OF HIS.
THEN AGAIN, I CAN'T JUST LEAVE
AND LET HIM TAKE THE STONE.
IF HE OBTAINS THE STONE'S POWER,
HE'D BECOME
PRACTICALLY INVINCIBLE.
I'D NEVER BE ABLE TO DEFEAT HIM.
( groans ) DAMN IT ALL.
I HAVE TO GET MY HANDS
ON WAMUU'S ANTIDOTE.
KARS WANTS TO KILL ME AFTER ALL.
WHY ME?
WAS THIS IN MY HOROSCOPE?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S IN THIS POCKET HERE?
OH. THE RED STONE OF AJA.
I HAVE WAITED A LONG TIME
FOR THIS, 5,000 YEARS,
AND AT LAST THE STONE IS MINE.
NOT THAT I EVER DOUBTED
IT WOULD BE.
IT WAS DESTINED
TO FALL INTO MY HANDS.
JoJo: KARS!
Kars: JUST BE PATIENT.
I'LL KILL YOU IN A MOMENT.
JoJo: DAMN, THAT BASTARD.
H‐HE REALLY HATES
EVERYTHING ABOUT ME.
LETTING HIM WALK AWAY
WITH THE STONE
WOULD MEAN THE END
FOR EVERYONE.
Von Stroheim: KARS, YOU FOOL.
DON'T THINK YOU'VE BEATEN ME,
BECAUSE I'M
NOT FINISHED WITH YOU YET.
♪
‐ ( whirring )
‐ Kars: HUH?
Von Stroheim: GERMAN SCIENCE
IS THE WORLD'S GREATEST!
I WILL BEAT YOU!
JoJo: VON STROHEIM, YOU IDIOT,
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
HOW CAN YOU SIT THERE
AND BOAST AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
Von Stroheim:
ULTRAVIOLET BEAMS, ACTIVATE!
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( Kars groans )
( JoJo gasps )
IT'S THE STONE!
HUH? OH, NO. THE STONE
IS SLIDING DOWN THE SLOPE.
( Von Stroheim gasps )
AH, DAMN IT, NO!
WE HAVE TO STOP IT.
THE STONE IS SLIDING
TOWARD THE CLIFF.
IF IT FALLS OFF,
IT COULD BE LOST FOREVER!
Caesar: WHAT THE HELL?
LOOK AT THIS.
Meshina:
W‐WHAT'S HAPPENED IN HERE?
Caesar: KARS HAPPENED.
Von Stroheim: JOJO,
YOU HAVE TO GO AFTER THE STONE!
GRAB IT WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
JoJo: DAMN. HE'S CATCHING UP.
HE'S FAST. HE'S FOCUSED
ON THE STONE LIKE A LASER.
THE WAY HE KEEPS ACCELERATING,
HE MUST BE PLANNING
TO GRAB THE STONE
AND FALL OFF THE CLIFF.
HE WON'T BE ABLE TO STOP
BEFORE HE REACHES THE EDGE.
D‐DAMN IT!
THE DROP BEYOND THAT CLIFF
IS AT LEAST
SEVERAL HUNDRED METERS.
WITH ALL HIS SUPERIOR ABILITIES,
KARS COULD SURVIVE THE FALL,
BUT IT'S AS HIGH AS JUMPING
OFF THE TALLEST SKYSCRAPER
WITHOUT A PARACHUTE.
IT'D BE CERTAIN DEATH FOR ME.
HE'S PASSING ME.
Von Stroheim:
JOJO PLANS TO SLOW DOWN
BEFORE HE REACHES THE EDGE
SO HE DOESN'T GO FLYING OFF,
BUT NOT KARS. JOJO CAN'T WIN.
JoJo: THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GONNA LET THIS SLIME
GET HIS HANDS ON THE STONE.
GO! RUN HARD, JOJO!
Kars: JOJO, WHEN I REACH DOWN
TO GRAB THE STONE,
I'LL BE OFF BALANCE.
WITH MY FLANK OPEN,
I'LL BE VULNERABLE.
IS THAT WHEN YOU'LL DO IT?
IS THAT WHEN
YOU'LL TRY TO KICK ME?
JoJo: HUH?
Kars: YOU'LL ATTACK ME
WITH YOUR HAMON,
EVEN IF IT MEANS THE STONE
DISAPPEARS INTO THE ABYSS.
( laughs )
YOU THINK YOUR PLAN
WILL WORK, JOJO?
( JoJo growls )
( Caesar gasps )
LOOK THERE. JOJO.
JoJo: YOU'RE RIGHT
ON THE NOSE, KARS.
HERE IT COMES!
IT'S THE KICK YOU ORDERED!
Von Stroheim: NO!
AH. HE'S USED HIS LEGS
TO PICK UP THE STONE
RIGHT AS JOJO KICKED HIM.
HE'S GOING TO GET AWAY WITH IT.
‐ I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
‐ ( Kars chuckles )
JoJo: NOW, KARS,
WHAT'S WITH THAT
RIDICULOUSLY ARROGANT GRIN?
I MEAN, I'M THE ONE
WHO SHOULD BE SMILING HERE.
I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE EXPECTED
AS MUCH FROM YOU.
A TRICK LIKE THAT REALLY
ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH TO FOOL ME.
MY KICK WASN'T AIMED
AT YOUR VULNERABLE FLANK,
BUT RATHER THE SNOW,
AND IT WORKED
JUST LIKE A BRAKE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
LOOKS LIKE I'M THE ONE WHO MADE
THE NICE CATCH, NOT YOU.
ENJOY YOUR TRIP, KARS.
UHH! AW, MAN. NO WAY!
AAH! A BLADE FROM HIS FOOT?!
Von Stroheim: JOJO!
( JoJo screams )
‐ Men: JOJO!
‐ ( Von Stroheim gasps )
HE'S FALLING WITH KARS.
JoJo: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
KARS'S BLADE IS STARTING
TO MELD ITSELF WITH MY BODY.
IT WON'T COME OUT.
( yells )
Y‐YOU SON OF A BITCH!
Narrator: IT'S 175 METERS
TO THE BOTTOM,
FIVE SECONDS UNTIL IMPACT.
JoJo: DAMN. FALLING TO MY DEATH
WITH THIS GUY?
( growls ) NO, THANK YOU.
CLINGING HAMON!
( gasps ) HE'S SO HEAVY.
Narrator: HAMON GOES
THROUGH FLUIDS EASILY,
BUT ICE AND SNOW ARE SOLID
AND IMPEDE THE HAMON.
BUT WATER IS
TRICKLING DOWN THE ICE,
SO THE HAMON CAN USE THAT
TO FLOW AROUND THE SOLIDS.
THUS IT'S WORKING PERFECTLY.
Kars: I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU DO.
THE STONE WILL BE MINE.
JoJo: THAT'S IT EXACTLY.
THAT TENACITY OF YOURS,
IT'S WHAT SCARES ME THE MOST.
I'M BEST AT EXPLOITING
MY OPPONENT'S NEGLIGENCE,
SO A TENACIOUS FOE
IS THE ABSOLUTE WORST
FOR ME TO FACE.
TENACITY IS THE OPPOSITE
OF NEGLIGENCE.
Kars: IT WILL BE MINE TODAY!
( JoJo yelps )
( screams )
( grunts )
MORE ICICLES UP AHEAD.
BEFORE I CAN DO ANYTHING,
I HAVE TO GET THIS BLADE
OUT OF MY SHOULDER.
WAIT. I CAN JUST SEND HAMON
THROUGH THE BLADE
AND DIRECTLY INTO KARS.
TAKE THIS!
Kars: AS I THOUGHT.
I KNEW YOU WOULD TRY
USING MY BLADE AGAINST ME.
JUST FOR THAT,
IT'S INTO THE CLIFF WALL
WITH YOU!
‐ AND NOW...
‐ JoJo: N‐NO. WAIT.
HE'S GONNA USE THAT BLADE
AND CUT ME INTO PIECES.
Caesar: KARS IS WAITING
FOR JOJO TO REBOUND
BEFORE HE STARTS CUTTING HIM.
THERE'S NO WAY
HE CAN DODGE THAT.
Kars: NOW I'M GOING
TO TAKE GREAT PLEASURE
IN SLICING YOU IN HALF
AND PICKING UP THE STONE
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE ABYSS.
( growls ) YOU...
( growls )
JoJo: NOW, YOU'RE NOT
ABOUT TO CUT THIS, ARE YOU?
YOU WOULDN'T DARE
TAKE THE CHANCE
OF CHOPPING THE STONE
IN HALF ALONG WITH ME.
I CAN USE YOUR OWN STRENGTH
AGAINST YOU
BY LETTING YOUR TENACITY ACT
AS A DEFENSIVE MEASURE FOR ME.
NOW EAT THIS, KARS! HAMON KICK!
♪
Kars: DAMN, HE'S TRYING TO USE
THE FALLING ICICLES AS A ROPE.
HE'S CLEVER...
BUT THEY'RE IN A FREEFALL, TOO.
HE'LL NEVER REACH THE TOP.
Caesar: IN THAT CASE,
ALLOW ME TO LEND A HAND.
HOLD ON.
Kars: HUH?
♪
JoJo: CAESAR!
Caesar: HEY, NICE TIMING,
DON'T YOU THINK, JOJO?
Von Stroheim:
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
AND WHAT ARE YOU TWO,
SOME KIND OF A TEAM?
Caesar: HEH.
FUSING FALLING ICICLES TOGETHER
TO MAKE A RESCUE ROPE,
I HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THAT.
ONLY JOJO WOULD TRY SOMETHING
THAT COLOSSALLY STUPID.
IT WAS PREDICTABLE.
( JoJo laughs )
AT LEAST YOU WERE ABLE
TO THINK UP A STUPID TRICK
AND THEN PULL IT OFF
IN THE NICK OF TIME.
I'M PROUD OF YOU, CAESAR.
Caesar: EH? WHAT WAS THAT?
JoJo: NICE. NICE.
REAL OUTSTANDING WORK,
CAESARINO.
AND, HEY, IF LISA LISA IS
UP THERE, GIVE HER A MESSAGE.
I'VE GOT THE RED STONE,
AND IT'S SAFE.
I KEPT HIM FROM SNATCHING IT.
Lisa Lisa:
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
ALL RIGHT, CAESAR,
YOU HAD BETTER PULL HIM UP NOW.
Meshina:
NOW, MY GERMAN COMPATRIOT,
YOUR BODY IS EVEN MORE DURABLE
THAN ANY OF THEIRS
COULD HOPE TO BE.
LISTEN. IF YOU CAN STOP
WITH THE SNOBBERY,
MAYBE WE CAN WORK TOGETHER.
( Von Stroheim grumbles )
( wind blowing )
( Kars laughing )
JOJO, YOU'RE A LUCKY ONE.
I'LL LET YOU
HOLD THE STONE FOR ME
FOR AT LEAST ANOTHER DAY.
♪
JoJo: SO THIS IS SWITZERLAND'S
FAMOUS SAINT MORITZ,
A WINTER SPORTS HUB
OFTEN REFERRED TO AS SUN VALLEY,
CHIC, RELAXED,
AND SOPHISTICATED,
A RESORT THAT THE WEALTHY
FLOCK TO DURING THE HOLIDAYS.
EVEN THE CATS LOOK LIKE
THEY'RE OWNED BY ACTRESSES
AND ARE PAMPERED AT ALL
THE FINEST SPAS IN EUROPE.
♪
AREN'T WE FUSSY?
NOT EVEN A TINY GLANCE
FOR SHRIMP?
THIS LITTLE PRINCESS
THINKS SHE'S THE CENTER
OF THE UNIVERSE,
BUT DOESN'T KNOW A THING
ABOUT THE WORLD AT ALL.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
WOULD THIS SMOKED SALMON
SUIT YOUR SNOOTY PALATE BETTER?
( cat meowing )
JoJo: THERE WE GO.
IT SEEMS I'VE FOUND
WHAT YOU PREFER.
THAT'S IT. REACH FOR IT.
JUST A LITTLE BIT HIGHER NOW.
STRETCH UP
JUST A LITTLE MORE THERE.
( cat meowing )
JoJo: I GOTCHA NOW.
( cat screeches )
( hisses )
JoJo: OH? DID I UPSET YOU?
ENJOY, YOU PUNY,
POMPOUS PUFFBALL.
( laughs )
♪
( sighs )
THAT WAS PRETTY MEAN.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA.
IT'S JUST BECAUSE
I'M REALLY ON EDGE.
WE ONLY HAVE FIVE DAYS
UNTIL THE RING DISSOLVES,
AND KARS IS ABSOLUTELY SERIOUS
ABOUT KILLING ME.
I CAN FEEL THE THREATS
CLOSING IN.
THEY'RE ALL AROUND.
I HAVE TO RELAX.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S ALWAYS SAYING
YOU CAN'T SIT AROUND
MOPING ABOUT STUFF.
Lisa Lisa: JOJO, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING JUST SITTING THERE?
GET UP OUT OF THAT CHAIR,
COME OVER HERE,
AND LOOK AT THIS.
JoJo: RIGHT.
BE THERE IN A SECOND.
Lisa Lisa: THE BUILDING
ON TOP OF THAT HILL
IS THE ADDRESS
ESIDISI PUT ON THE PACKAGE.
Meshina: IT LOOKS LIKE
THE ABANDONED CORPSE
OF A SHUTTERED HOTEL.
IT WOULD MAKE A PERFECT HIDEOUT
FOR KARS DURING DAYLIGHT HOURS.
EVERY DOORWAY AND WINDOW
IS BOARDED UP.
NO SUNLIGHT
COULD GET IN THERE.
Caesar: THAT'S GOT TO BE IT.
I'M SURE KARS
HIDES IN THERE DURING THE DAY.
I BET HE'S JUST SITTING INSIDE,
WAITING FOR WAMUU TO SHOW UP.
Lisa Lisa: ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT IS THE PLAN?
Caesar: HUMPH.
THAT'S A NO‐BRAINER.
WE SHOULD ATTACK NOW.
Meshina: YES, I AGREE.
KARS CAN'T GO OUTSIDE
AS LONG AS THE SUN IS UP,
AND THAT GIVES US
A TREMENDOUS ADVANTAGE.
Lisa Lisa: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
JoJo: SORRY, BUT...
‐ I HAVE TO DISAGREE WITH YOU.
‐ ( all gasp )
JoJo: YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THIS WRONG.
I THINK IT'S MORE DANGEROUS
TO ATTACK WHEN THE SUN IS UP.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
KARS HAS BEEN LIVING LIKE THIS
FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS.
HE WOULDN'T HAVE SURVIVED
IF HE HAD LEFT HIMSELF
DEFENSELESS DURING THE DAY.
Caesar: OH, PLEASE!
JoJo: WALKING INTO HIS HIDEOUT
AND TRYING TO TAKE HIM DOWN
RIGHT NOW WOULD BE SUICIDAL.
I'M NOT GOING TO DO IT.
IT WOULD BE LIKE A BUG WALKING
INTO A SPIDER'S WEB ON PURPOSE.
Caesar: HAH! COME ON.
JOJO, THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU.
ARE YOU SCARED OR SOMETHING?
JoJo: I THINK I'M GOING TO TAKE
SUN TZU'S ADVICE THIS TIME.
ONLY ENGAGE IN A FIGHT
WHEN VICTORY IS ASSURED.
LIKE I SAID, I'M NOT GOING IN.
Caesar: OH, YEAH?
SO YOU'RE CHICKENING OUT?
JoJo: I'M NOT AFRAID.
I'M JUST THINKING STRAIGHT.
I'VE GOT A COOL HEAD,
UNLIKE YOU.
CAESAR, WE HAVE TO WAIT
FOR HIM TO MAKE HIS MOVE FIRST.
Caesar: AN ASSURED VICTORY
IS WHAT YOU WANT?
KARS IS ALL ALONE THERE.
IT'S HIM AGAINST ALL OF US.
THAT'S A FOUR‐TO‐ONE ADVANTAGE.
WE HAVE TO STRIKE NOW,
BEFORE WAMUU ARRIVES,
CUTTING THAT IN HALF.
JoJo: CALM DOWN.
DON'T GO OFF ALL CRAZY NOW.
TRY AND KEEP YOUR HEAD TOGETHER.
JUST FOCUS,
AND THINK IT THROUGH.
IF WE GO NOW,
HE'LL CUT US TO PIECES.
YOU CAN'T APPROACH THIS
HALF‐COCKED.
Caesar: I AM NOT HALF‐COCKED!
I'M GONNA END THIS!
I AM GOING TO FINALLY
FINISH THE FIGHT
THAT CUT SHORT THE LIVES
OF BOTH OF OUR GRANDFATHERS!
I'M GONNA DESTROY KARS!
YOU'RE GOING TO FINISH IT?
RIGHT, AND WHY BRING OUR
DEAD GRANDFATHERS INTO THIS?
WHO THE HELL CARES?!
DON'T DRAG THE DEAD INTO
YOUR LITTLE DRAMA, YOU MORON.
( Caesar grunts )
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO ME?
JoJo: FAMILY YOU'VE NEVER MET
AND THAT CAME LONG BEFORE
YOUR TIME DOESN'T MEAN CRAP.
IT'S JUST FOOLISH.
ONLY A COMPLETE IDIOT WOULD DIE
FOR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
( Caesar growls )
‐ ( both gasp )
‐ Meshina: CAESAR?
Caesar: YOU WATCH
YOUR MOUTH, JOJO!
( JoJo groans )
HEY, WHAT WAS THAT FOR, YOU‐‐
A SUCKER PUNCH, HUH?
Caesar: OH, IT'S ON.
JoJo: WHAT THE HELL, CAESAR?!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?!
Caesar: JUST SHUT THE HELL UP!
Lisa Lisa: CAESAR, STOP IT. NOW.
Meshina: YOU TOO, JOJO!
Lisa Lisa: CAESAR!
JoJo: YOU BASTARD,
WHAT'S WITH YOU?
HAVE YOU COMPLETELY LOST IT?
YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE SOME KIND OF A MADMAN.
Caesar: JOJO, I GUESS YOU WON'T
EVER UNDERSTAND THE CONCEPT
OF FAMILY HONOR AND
INHERITING A BATTLE LIKE THIS.
JoJo: HUH?
( Caesar scoffs )
ENOUGH. I'M GOING.
Lisa Lisa: CAESAR,
JOJO IS RIGHT.
IT'S FAR TOO DANGEROUS.
WE HAVE NO WAY OF KNOWING
WHAT MIGHT BE WAITING
FOR US IN THERE.
WE'LL WAIT FOR KARS
TO MAKE HIS MOVE.
THAT IS AN ORDER, CAESAR.
THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERS NOW
IS PROTECTING
THE RED STONE OF AJA.
Caesar: NO, COACH, I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T OBEY THIS TIME.
YOU KNOW THIS IS A MATTER
OF BLOOD AND FAMILY HONOR.
IT'S A ZEPPELI PROBLEM.
I JUST CAN'T LEAVE IT UNSETTLED
WHEN I KNOW
EXACTLY WHERE KARS IS HIDING.
I CAN'T SIT HERE
TWIRLING MY THUMBS,
WAITING FOR HIM TO COME TO ME!
( grunts )
Meshina: WHAT DO WE DO?
Lisa Lisa: FOLLOW HIM,
AND DO WHATEVER YOU HAVE TO
TO STOP HIM FROM ENTERING,
EVEN IF IT MEANS USING FORCE.
( JoJo sighs ) CAESAR,
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
WHY ARE YOU SO DAMN GRIM
AND HOTHEADED ALL OF A SUDDEN?
WHY CAN'T YOU BE PATIENT
AND JUST WAIT A WHILE?
Lisa Lisa: YOU SEE,
YOU'VE INADVERTENTLY TOUCHED
ON A PAINFUL PIECE
OF HIS HIDDEN PAST.
ALTHOUGH YOU DIDN'T MEAN TO,
YOU'VE HIT UPON A DARK PLACE
WHERE HE HARBORS
HIS SADDEST SECRETS.
JoJo: CAESAR HAS A HIDDEN PAST?
♪
W‐WHAT THE HELL COULD IT BE?
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Caesar: I FEEL
LIKE I DID BACK THEN
WHEN I WAS NA ÏVE AND POOR!
I'LL USE MY VICIOUSNESS
TO DESTROY YOU!
Wamuu: VERY WELL.
YOU ARE WORTHY
OF DEATH AT MY HANDS,
BUBBLE USER!