♪
Caesar: YOU MONSTERS!
DON'T TURN YOUR BACKS ON ME!
Wamuu: HMM?
Caesar: FINE THEN.
I'LL SAVOR THIS ONE!
HAMON BUBBLE LAUNCHER!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Wamuu: COULD‐‐COULD THIS BE‐‐
IS THIS WHAT I THINK?
JoJo: NICE WORK.
CAESAR MAY BE A NARCISSIST,
BUT HIS HAMON SKILLS ARE SOLID.
Caesar: THESE BUBBLES
MAY LOOK HARMLESS,
BUT PREPARE FOR A BOMBARDMENT!
( Wamuu growls )
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( Caesar gasps )
Speedwagon: HE‐‐
HE POPPED THEM ALL.
HOW ON EARTH DID HE DO THAT?
Caesar: THAT'S NOT HIS HAIR.
THOSE ARE WIRES ATTACHED
TO HIS HEAD HE'S MANIPULATING.
HE POPPED MY BUBBLES WITH
THE WIND THAT THEY CREATED.
Speedwagon: BUT THEN THAT MEANS
THEY WERE DESIGNED
TO BE ANTI‐HAMON WEAPONS.
SOMEHOW THEY'RE ALREADY FAMILIAR
WITH THE PRINCIPLES OF HAMON.
THEY MUST HAVE FACED HAMON
AT SOME POINT
OVER 2,000 YEARS AGO.
( Caesar gasps )
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO THE AIR AROUND THEM?
Speedwagon: CAESAR, LOOK OUT!
GET DOWN!
( Caesar gasps )
WH‐WHAT THE...
Speedwagon: COVER YOUR EYES!
THAT WASN'T JUST WIND!
IT WAS THE AFTERMATH
OF A POWERFUL VORTEX
THAT'S STILL ACTIVE!
( Caesar gasping )
Speedwagon: CAESAR!
Kars: THESE HUMANS KNOW HAMON.
Esidisi: I THOUGHT
WE DESTROYED ALL THE MEMBERS
OF THE HAMON TRIBE
2,000 YEARS AGO.
AND YET HERE THEY ARE,
READY TO WELCOME US
AT OUR OWN AWAKENING.
( Caesar groans )
DAMN...YOU.
YOU KILLED HIM.
YOU KILLED MY FRIEND.
DO YOU THINK LOSING AN EYE
WILL STOP ME?!
( Pillar Men chuckling )
Caesar: STOP.
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?!
( Wamuu laughs )
YOU ALL HAVE MEMORIZED
YOUR HAMON HANDBOOK VERY WELL.
YOU ALWAYS SAY THE SAME THING.
IT WAS THAT WAY WHEN WE CROSSED
FROM THE WESTERN CONTINENT,
AND IT IS THAT WAY NOW STILL.
"YOU THINK LOSING AN ARM OR
AN EYE OR A LEG WILL STOP ME?
"HOW DARE YOU TAKE
MY FRIEND'S LIFE?
DON'T YOU KNOW
HOW MUCH I LOVED HIM?"
THAT'S WHY WE LAUGH, HUMAN.
Caesar: YOU‐‐YOU BASTARDS!
Kars: IGNORE HIM.
WE'RE ON A QUEST
TO FIND THE STONE.
Caesar: WHAT?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
FACE ME, COWARDS!
( gags )
Wamuu: YOU'RE MOST VULNERABLE
IN YOUR THROAT AND YOUR LUNGS.
WE KNOW
THAT IF YOU CAN'T BREATHE,
THEN YOUR HAMON
IS RENDERED USELESS.
BUT BECAUSE I CANNOT RESIST
A WORTHY OPPONENT, HEAR ME.
I SHALL SPARE YOU, BECAUSE I
LONG FOR THE OPPORTUNITY
TO MEET YOU AGAIN
WHEN YOU ARE STRONGER.
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET,
I WANT TO ADMIRE YOUR STRENGTH.
I WANT YOU TO BECOME WORTHY
OF MY TIME
SO THAT I MIGHT DESTROY YOU
WITH GREAT HONOR.
( Caesar panting )
Wamuu: IT APPEARS THAT HE
WAS THE ONLY HAMON USER.
Kars: HMM. LET'S MOVE.
( JoJo clearing his throat )
SORRY. I JUST CAN'T SEEM
TO SHAKE THIS COUGH.
MAYBE IT'S THE HAMON TRAINING
THAT'S MAKING ME ILL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
( footsteps )
HMM.
HE ONLY SLICED YOUR EYELID.
THE ACTUAL EYEBALL ITSELF
IS JUST FINE.
PERHAPS YOU
SHOULD SIT THIS ONE OUT.
I THINK WE'VE ALL SEEN ENOUGH
OF THE BUBBLE LAUNCHER
FOR ONE DAY.
WATCH AND LEARN AS I
TAKE CARE OF THIS ONE MYSELF.
Speedwagon: JOJO!
JoJo: JUST CALM DOWN,
SPEEDWAGON.
THIS GUY IS ASKING FOR IT.
IT'S TIME FOR ME TO SHOW OFF
THE BRAND‐NEW TECHNIQUE
‐ I'VE BEEN WORKING ON.
‐ Caesar: WHAT?
JoJo: PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
MY NAME IS JOSEPH JOESTAR,
AND THESE ARE THE HANDS
KNOWN FOR DEFEATING
YOUR MATE, SANTVIENTO.
♪
( balls clanking )
I CALL THIS MOVE
MY HAMON CLACKER VOLLEY.
I START OFF BY FILLING
THESE LITTLE CLACKER BALLS HERE
WITH A BIT OF HAMON.
WUH‐WHAH!
OH, NO!
Speedwagon: JOJO, WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
THIS IS NO TIME FOR GAMES.
Caesar: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JoJo: NOT INTENTIONALLY.
I'M TRYING TO BE SERIOUS.
CAESAR, I AM TRULY SORRY
FOR THE LOSS OF YOUR FRIEND.
I UNDERSTAND
BOTH YOUR PAIN AND YOUR ANGER.
ADDITIONALLY, THESE GUYS
MAY BE THE BIGGEST GROUP
OF EGOTISTICAL JACKASSES
I'VE EVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
I MAY NOT BE
A MASTER OF THIS YET,
BUT I'LL STILL KNOCK YOU
INTO NEXT TUESDAY
WITH MY CLACKER VOLLEY!
( Wamuu grunts )
JoJo: I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
BUT I KNOW THAT MY HAMON
IS RELATIVELY WEAK.
I'M PRETTY SURE I CAN MAKE UP
FOR WHAT I'M LACKING
WITH THESE STEEL CLACKERS.
IF I CAN JUST BREAK OPEN
YOUR SKIN EVEN A LITTLE
AND FILL YOU WITH HAMON,
THAT SHOULD EVEN UP MY HANDICAP,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I CAN TELL YOU'RE NERVOUS.
TAKE THAT!
♪
( growls )
( Esidisi laughs )
WELL, THAT WAS FUN.
Kars: LET US KEEP MOVING.
APPARENTLY THE HUMAN RACE HAS
REGRESSED RATHER THAN EVOLVED.
Wamuu: QUITE AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
( chuckles )
AMUSING, THOUGH.
( JoJo sputters )
Caesar: JOJO,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOUR CHILDISH LITTLE GAMES
ARE GOING TO GET US ALL KILLED.
Speedwagon: HE'S PLAYING COY,
BUT THIS MAY ACTUALLY BE
THE BEST JOJO'S GOT.
HE'D BE FINE IF HE WAS FACING
SOME COMMON STREET PUNK,
BUT I DON'T THINK HE REALIZES
THAT THESE OPPONENTS ARE
ON A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT LEVEL.
IT WOULD BE COMICAL
IF IT WEREN'T SO TRAGIC.
JoJo: WHY ISN'T ANYONE TAKING
MY LITTLE METAL BALLS SERIOUSLY?
THAT'S FAR ENOUGH.
DON'T MAKE ME
CLACK YOU INTO THE GROUND.
Wamuu: STOP.
DON'T YOU FEEL THAT HUMAN LIVES
ARE SHORT ENOUGH?
THERE'S NO NEED
TO SPRINT TO YOUR DEATH.
JoJo: SILENCE. IF YOU'VE EVER
HAD SPAGHETTI AL NERO DI SEPPIA,
YOU KNOW IT LOOKS BAD,
BUT IT'S DELICIOUS.
YOU SHOULD TASTE
MY CLACKER VOLLEY
BEFORE YOU JUDGE IT.
♪
( men gasp )
Caesar: THE CLACKERS,
THEY VANISHED.
JoJo: ♪ I'VE BEEN TRAINING
ON MY HAMON ♪
♪ ALL THE LIVE‐LONG DAY
Caesar: HE'S INSANE.
( ropes stretching )
Wamuu: HMM?
JoJo: WELL, LOOKIT, MA.
NO HANDS.
WHERE ARE THE CLACKERS?
( laughs )
A TRUE MAGICIAN...
NEVER REVEALS HIS SECRET!
EAT THIS!
( bones pop )
( gasps )
Speedwagon: HOW CAN
ANYTHING MOVE LIKE THAT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M SEEING.
HE'S FASTER THAN SANTVIENTO.
Caesar: I DON'T THINK
THOSE IDIOTIC CLACKERS
DID SO MUCH AS GRAZE HIM.
( Wamuu laughs )
I ADMIRE YOUR WEAPON,
YOUR COURAGE,
AND YOUR CREATIVITY, HUMAN.
I'M ACTUALLY ENJOYING
YOUR COMPANY.
YOU DESERVE TIME.
ONE MINUTE, BUT ONLY ONE,
THAT IS HOW MUCH TIME
I WILL ALLOW YOU
TO FIGHT THE MIGHTY WAMUU.
( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( screams )
‐ Caesar and Speedwagon: JOJO!
Wamuu: I SHALL USE
YOUR WOUND AS A TIMER.
YOUR WRIST WILL WORK WELL
AS A TIMEKEEPING DEVICE,
AND YOU WILL LOSE CONSCIOUSNESS
DUE TO A LOSS OF BLOOD
IN EXACTLY ONE MINUTE.
SHOW ME WHAT YOU CAN DO, HUMAN.
( JoJo gasps )
Wamuu: THIS IS WHAT I OFTEN TOLD
THE MEMBERS
OF THE HAMON TRIBE,
"YOUR LIFE IS NOW MY HOURGLASS
MEASURED IN BLOOD."
Kars: WAMUU,
WE'LL BE WAITING OUTSIDE.
Wamuu: NOW, BOY, GO AHEAD,
AND RETRIEVE
YOUR WEAPON QUICKLY.
JoJo: WHAT? I'M SORRY.
I'M GROWING DEAF IN THIS EAR.
IT ALMOST SOUNDED LIKE YOU SAID,
"GO AHEAD,
AND RETRIEVE YOUR WEAPON,"
WHICH WOULD BE RIDICULOUS.
I MEAN, WHY WOULD
YOU RETRIEVE SOMETHING
THAT COMES RIGHT BACK TO YOU?
Wamuu: HMM?
( groans )
( both gasp )
JoJo: LOOKS LIKE MY CLACKER
BOOMERANG WORKED PRETTY WELL.
I SHOULDN'T EVEN NEED
THE FULL MINUTE
TO DESTROY YOU NOW. ( grunts )
THAT'S FOR KILLING
CAESAR'S FRIEND,
THAT'S FOR
NOT TAKING ME SERIOUSLY,
AND THAT'S BECAUSE I'M SICK
OF LOOKING AT YOUR UGLY FACE!
Wamuu: DO WHAT YOU MUST.
I DESERVE AS MUCH.
NO OPPONENT
HAS EVER STRUCK MY FACE,
AND THIS IS THE PRICE
FOR MY CARELESSNESS.
I SHALL TAKE THIS BEATING
IN ORDER TO PROPERLY HONOR YOU
BEFORE I DESTROY YOU.
JoJo: YOU SAY THAT NO ONE
HAS EVER HIT YOU
IN THAT UGLY MUG OF YOURS?
WHAT AN HONOR.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN STOP TO BLINK
WHEN YOU KILLED CAESAR'S FRIEND
MARK, DID YOU? YOU MONSTER!
DO YOU NOT VALUE LIFE AT ALL?!
Speedwagon:
JOJO, WATCH YOURSELF!
HIS ARM ISN'T BROKEN!
HE'S GETTING READY TO USE IT!
( JoJo gasps )
♪
WHOA. I HAVE A FEELING
THIS ISN'T GOOD FOR ME.
Wamuu:
A CHARMING OBSERVATION, HUMAN.
I'M NOW SCARRED
DUE TO MY CARELESSNESS.
IT WAS MY DUTY
TO ALLOW YOU TO PUMMEL ME
AS PUNISHMENT
FOR MY OWN LACK OF JUDGMENT.
THAT HAS NOW ENDED, HOWEVER.
Speedwagon: JOJO, FINISH HIM NOW
WHILE YOU STILL CAN!
Wamuu: MY ULTIMATE TECHNIQUE,
THE DIVINE SANDSTORM!
JoJo: GUHH! I DON'T LIKE
THE SOUND OF THAT.
Narrator: HE STARTS BY SPINNING
HIS LEFT ARM CLOCKWISE
AND THEN HIS RIGHT ARM
COUNTERCLOCKWISE.
JOJO IS UNPREPARED TO COUNTER
A TECHNIQUE LIKE THIS,
AS WAMUU'S FISTS SEEM
TO GROW BEFORE HIS EYES.
( JoJo yells )
Narrator: THE AIR
BETWEEN WAMUU'S ARMS
TRANSFORMS INTO A POWERFUL
VORTEX OF DESTRUCTION.
THIS VACUUM CREATES A HIGHLY
PRESSURIZED, DEADLY MAELSTROM.
JoJo: GREAT, IF HE CAN TEAR
THROUGH MARBLE PILLARS,
I DON'T SEE MYSELF
HAVING MUCH OF A CHANCE
AGAINST A WINDSTORM LIKE THIS.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN
ANYTHING THIS POWERFUL!
Speedwagon: UHH. JOJO.
♪
Wamuu: I CALL THAT
DIVINE SANDSTORM.
Speedwagon: NO! JOJO!
Caesar: DON'T BE A DAMN FOOL.
RUN, SPEEDWAGON. GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
I'LL TRY
AND DISTRACT HIM SOMEHOW.
Wamuu: CURSE THIS BLOOD
IN MY EYE. THREW OFF MY AIM.
BUT IT PROVED ENOUGH
WHEN YOU MADE THE CHOICE
TO HIDE BEHIND A PILLAR.
HMM. YOU DIED QUICKLY.
NORMALLY I WOULD IGNORE HUMAN
ONLOOKERS SUCH AS YOURSELVES.
HOWEVER, YOU WITNESSED MY SHAME,
SO UNFORTUNATELY I MUST TAKE
THE TIME TO DESTROY YOU BOTH.
YOU MAY PRAY NOW IF YOU WISH.
( both gasp )
Wamuu: EH?
HMM. MUST BE THE LIGHT.
♪
( JoJo panting )
Caesar: WHAT DOES
HE THINK HE'S DOING?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
HE'S ACTUALLY TRYING TO ESCAPE.
Wamuu: HUH?
HMM.
Caesar: THAT COWARD HAS NO SHAME
PLAYING DEAD LIKE THAT.
I UNDERSTAND LEAVING ME,
BUT WHAT ABOUT SPEEDWAGON?
I KNEW HE WAS SPINELESS.
JoJo: THIS GUY IS THE MOST
POWERFUL FOE I'VE EVER FACED.
MY BREATHING IS OUT OF CONTROL.
I CAN'T CONTROL MY HAMON.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE
ANY OTHER OPTION LEFT.
LUCKILY, MY SPECIALTY
IS RUNNING AWAY.
Narrator: BEHOLD
OUR NOW‐BROKEN HERO,
JOJO, FORCED TO PLAY DEAD,
CRAWLING FOR HIS LIFE,
AND NOW LEAVING SPEEDWAGON
BEHIND TO FACE CERTAIN DEATH.
EVEN WITH ALL OF THIS,
JOJO REMAINS DEDICATED,
A HERO WORTHY OF THIS TALE.
HOW IS THAT, YOU ASK?
( JoJo grunts )
( clatter )
( Wamuu growls )
NICE TRY THERE, HUMAN.
YOU COWARD.
NO TRUE WARRIOR WOULD EVER FEIGN
DEATH JUST TO SAVE HIMSELF.
HMM?
( JoJo laughs )
THAT MAY BE TRUE,
THOUGH MY INTENTION WAS NOT
TO ESCAPE, BUT TO DISTRACT.
TRUTH BE TOLD, I WAS JUST TRYING
TO GET YOU ONTO THIS MINE CART.
Wamuu: YOU ARE CLEVER INDEED.
SO YOU WERE ONLY
PLAYING THE PART OF THE COWARD
TO LURE ME AWAY FROM
YOUR FRIENDS. IS THAT RIGHT?
JoJo: I'M SURPRISED
YOU FELL FOR IT.
THAT TRICK IS
PROBABLY OLDER THAN YOU.
( thinking )
GET OUT NOW, SPEEDWAGON. RUN!
CAESAR, GO!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
Speedwagon: JOJO.
Caesar: THAT BASTARD.
WHAT A NOBLE MOVE.
JoJo: NOW THAT I'VE PAINTED
MYSELF INTO A CORNER HERE,
I NEED TO COME UP
WITH A SECOND PART TO MY PLAN,
WHICH WOULD BE...
( Wamuu laughs )
Narrator: THE UNFLAPPABLE HERO.
HE CALMLY SEARCHES FOR OPTIONS,
NOT KNOWING WHAT TO DO NEXT,
BUT HIS WILL REMAINS UNBROKEN.
Speedwagon: JOJO!
Caesar: DAMN YOU, JOJO.
HE'S IN FAR WORSE SHAPE
THAN I AM.
( grunts) I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
THE ONE TO LURE WAMUU AWAY.
I SEE NOW THAT JOJO
ONLY ACTS FOOLISHLY
TO CONFOUND HIS OPPONENT.
HE MUST ACTUALLY
HAVE A GOOD PLAN
TO BEAT THOSE MONSTERS.
( JoJo panting )
Wamuu: ALTHOUGH YOU
ARE QUITE CONFIDENT
FOR SOMEONE WHO IS KNOCKING
ON DEATH'S DOOR,
I MUST TELL YOU
THAT YOUR PLAN IS A POOR ONE.
YOU'RE QUITE TOUGH.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
SOFTHEADED,
BUT TOUGH NONETHELESS.
TELL ME,
HOW DO YOU REMAIN UNYIELDING
IN THE MOMENTS
BEFORE YOUR DEATH?
IS IT BECAUSE YOU
HAVE BRICKS FOR BRAINS,
OR DO YOU STILL HAVE
ANOTHER TRICK FOR ME?
JoJo: DO YOU REALLY
WANT TO KNOW?
Wamuu: ACTUALLY, NO.
LET ME GUESS.
BECAUSE YOU'RE
SO OBVIOUSLY CLEVER,
I'LL GIVE YOU
THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT
THAT YOU
WOULDN'T BE STUPID ENOUGH
TO BE HOLDING A STICK
OF DYNAMITE BEHIND YOUR BACK.
JoJo: DAMN. HE'S ONTO ME.
Wamuu: AND I KNOW YOU WOULDN'T
INSULT MY INTELLIGENCE
BY THINKING YOU
COULD QUICKLY THROW THE BRAKE
AND SEND THE MINE CART
FLYING OFF THE TRACKS,
MAYBE LIKE THIS!
( JoJo screams )
DAMN. HE GOT ME THERE, TOO.
( mine car clatters )
Pillar Men: HMM?
Wamuu: THE TIME
ON YOUR HOURGLASS WRIST
IS JUST ABOUT UP.
THERE IS ABSOLUTELY NO CHANCE
THAT YOU WILL SURVIVE THIS
ANY LONGER.
I FOUND YOUR TRICKS
TO BE VERY QUAINT.
BEFORE YOU DIE, TELL ME,
WHY DO I STILL NOT SEE DEFEAT
IN YOUR EYES?
JoJo: I'LL TELL YOU IF YOU WANT,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SAY, "PLEASE," FIRST.
Wamuu: MORE GAMES.
YOU'VE TESTED ME LONG ENOUGH.
‐ PREPARE TO DIE.
‐ JoJo: SUCH A SHAME,
BECAUSE A MONTH FROM NOW,
I CAN GUARANTEE THAT I
WOULD BE ABLE TO DESTROY YOU.
Wamuu: WHAT WAS THAT?
JoJo: WITH JUST
ONE MORE MONTH OF TRAINING,
I WOULD ANNIHILATE YOU.
I WAS THE FIRST PERSON TO HIT,
AS WELL AS THE FIRST
TO SCAR YOUR FACE.
WHEN I PUT MY MIND TO SOMETHING,
I CAN ACCOMPLISH
PRETTY MUCH ANYTHING.
OH, WELL.
I GUESS NONE OF THAT
REALLY MATTERS NOW.
SO CAN WE JUST
GET THIS OVER WITH?
IT WILL BE AN HONOR TO BE KILLED
BY A WARRIOR LIKE YOU,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
Wamuu: WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THIS?
JoJo: OH, I'M SICK AND TIRED
OF ALL THIS TALKING.
JUST HURRY UP,
AND MAKE IT PAINLESS, WAMUU.
Wamuu: EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO GET AT?
♪
Caesar: I DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT HE'S STILL ALIVE.
JoJo: IS IT TRUE
THAT YOU PILLAR MEN
OFTEN LIVE FOR MILLENNIA?
THAT'S A LONG TIME TO BE
WALKING AROUND WITH THE SHAME
OF HAVING YOUR FACE
REARRANGED BY A LOWLY HUMAN.
IT SEEMS TO ME THAT THE ONLY WAY
YOU COULD REGAIN YOUR HONOR
WOULD BE
BY DEFEATING ME IN A FIGHT
AFTER I'VE UNDERGONE
PROPER HAMON TRAINING.
Wamuu: I DO NOT
HAVE TO DEFEAT YOU
IN ORDER TO MAINTAIN MY HONOR.
JoJo: HIS ENTIRE BODY
IS SHAKING WITH RAGE.
I HAVE A CHANCE
IF I CAN MAKE HIM THINK
HIS INTEGRITY IS AT STAKE.
HE GAVE HIMSELF AWAY
AS THE PROUD WARRIOR TYPE
THE MOMENT
HE CALLED ME A COWARD.
PRIDE IS HIS ACHILLES HEEL.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU NOTICED,
BUT I'M STILL NEW AT THIS.
HOWEVER, IF I TRAINED
WITH MY HAMON FOR A MONTH,
I KNOW I COULD GIVE YOU
THE FAIR FIGHT
A WARRIOR LIKE YOU DESERVES.
THE FIRST PERSON
WHO EVER HIT YOU IN THE FACE
GAVE YOU A NASTY SCAR.
IT WOULD BE A SHAME
IF YOU KILLED THAT PERSON
BEFORE HE'S WORTHY.
BUT IF YOU FEEL
THE NEED TO KILL ME
BEFORE I HAVE A CHANCE
TO BATTLE YOU AS AN EQUAL,
THEN GO AHEAD AND DO
WHATEVER YOU NEED TO DO.
( Wamuu growls )
YOU BASTARD!
Esidisi: WAMUU.
Wamuu: MASTER ESIDISI.
Esidisi: YOU GAVE
THIS HUMAN ONE MINUTE.
WHY MUST YOU INSIST
ON LETTING HIM TOY WITH YOU? EH?
JoJo: JUST GO AWAY.
I ALMOST HAD HIM.
( growls )
Wamuu: HMM.
( JoJo gasps )
( Wamuu exhales )
MASTER ESIDISI,
I HAVE GROWN FOND
OF THIS PARTICULAR MEMBER
OF THE HAMON TRIBE.
JoJo: I GOT HIM.
Wamuu: JOJO,
YOU WILL BE HAPPY TO KNOW
THAT I HAVE DECIDED
TO ACCEPT YOUR PROPOSITION.
IF YOU SWEAR THAT YOU
WILL TRAIN YOUR HARDEST
TO FULFILL YOUR POTENTIAL,
THEN I WILL GIVE YOU
EXACTLY ONE MONTH TO DO SO.
JoJo: SO YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO KILL ME NOW?
Wamuu: THAT'S RIGHT.
JoJo: BUT WE'RE GOING
TO FIGHT AGAIN?
Wamuu: WE ARE.
JoJo: ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
I'LL GIVE YOU A CHANCE
TO TAKE IT BACK.
( thinking ) YES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S WORKING.
Wamuu: HOWEVER...
I WILL NEED ASSURANCES
THAT YOU WILL NOT TRY
TO RUN AWAY AGAIN, OF COURSE.
Esidisi: HEH HEH. NICE, WAMUU.
I WAS WONDERING WHEN YOU
WOULD FINALLY PROPOSE.
Wamuu: SAY HELLO
TO THE WEDDING RING OF DEATH.
GUESS WHERE IT GOES.
A HINT, NOT ON YOUR FINGER.
JoJo: W‐WHAT ARE YOU
DOING WITH THAT?!
( crack )
Wamuu: THIS RING WILL START
TO DISSOLVE IN 33 DAYS.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO REMOVE,
AND ONCE DISSOLVED,
IT WILL RELEASE
A VIRULENT POISON.
ANY ATTEMPT
TO REMOVE OR DAMAGE IT
WILL ALSO RELEASE
THE LETHAL POISON.
( JoJo gags )
Wamuu: HOWEVER,
THERE IS ONE CERTAIN WAY
TO DISSOLVE THE RING
WITHOUT HARM.
SIMPLY BATTLE AND DEFEAT ME
WITHIN 33 DAYS,
AND I SHALL GIVE YOU
THE ANTIDOTE
THAT I KEEP INSIDE THE HOLLOW
OF MY LIP RING.
Caesar: JOJO!
Wamuu: THE VOW
ON THAT WEDDING RING
STATES, "TILL DEATH
DO US PART," JOJO.
BE AT THE COLOSSEUM IN 33 DAYS.
MEET ME THERE AT MIDNIGHT,
AND WE SHALL BATTLE
AS EQUALS, JOJO.
( Esidisi chuckles )
I HOPE YOU DIDN'T THINK
YOUR PALTRY TRICKS
WOULD HELP YOU ESCAPE, HUMAN.
I DON'T IMAGINE
THE TWO OF US WILL FIGHT,
BUT JUST IN CASE,
HERE'S A GIFT FOR YOU...
( JoJo gags )
Esidisi: ONE THAT FITS
PERFECTLY AROUND YOUR WINDPIPE!
JoJo: AGH!
MY HEART AND MY THROAT!
Esidisi: MY POISON IS
QUITE DIFFERENT FROM WAMUU'S,
AND I KEEP THE ANTIDOTE FOR THAT
POISON IN MY NOSE RING.
KARS? WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO NEXT?
Kars: I DON'T THINK SO.
IMMORTALITY
CAN BE BORING AT TIMES.
TO ENCOUNTER A WORTHY OPPONENT,
THAT IS BOTH SUCH A RARE
AND TANTALIZING THOUGHT,
A GIFT THAT WOULD GIVE
OUR LIVES MEANING.
I CAN SEE WHY YOU DO THIS.
HOWEVER, DO NOT FORGET
THAT OUR GOAL
IS TO OBTAIN
THE RED STONE OF AJA.
WE MUST STAY FOCUSED. LET'S GO.
Wamuu:
TRAIN LONG AND HARD, JOJO,
SO YOU CAN CHALLENGE
MY DIVINE SANDSTORM.
( Esidisi laughing )
( JoJo panting )
I‐I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT.
TWO WEDDING RINGS WITH POISON?
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE SOME KIND
OF SICK JOKE OR SOMETHING?
I'VE GOT ONE AROUND MY THROAT
AND ONE AROUND MY HEART.
DO THESE GUYS THINK
I'M SOME KIND OF BIGAMIST,
OR MAYBE‐‐( groans )
WELL, AT LEAST SPEEDWAGON
AND CAESAR ARE SAFE.
THAT'S WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
NO SENSE
IN FEELING SORRY FOR MYSELF.
( footsteps )
( Caesar gasps )
JOJO.
YOU FOOL.
THAT WAS ONE HELL OF A BLUFF
YOU JUST PULLED THERE.
THE BEST CON MAN COULDN'T
HAVE DONE IT BETTER THAN YOU.
YOU ACTED BRAVELY,
BUT NOW YOU'LL NEED
TO BACK IT UP.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME TO WORK,
AND WE HAVE SERIOUS
HAMON TRAINING AHEAD.
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ THEY STAND THERE
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
AND I'LL BE THERE ♪
♪
JoJo: WHEN I SAID
I NEEDED A MONTH,
I ONLY MEANT IT AS A BLUFF!
Woman: WELL, FROM UP HERE,
IT'S REALLY MORE DEEP THAN TALL.
Caesar: COACH, WAIT!
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS!
JoJo: BECAUSE YOU'RE A GIRL,
DOESN'T MEAN
THAT I WON'T GIVE YOU
WHAT YOU DESERVE.
Woman: WELCOME TO VENICE.