Narrator: BEHOLD THE VILLAGE
OF WIND KNIGHTS LOT,
NESTLED IN A VALLEY
AND RINGED BY DAUNTING CLIFFS.
A CASTLE DOMINATES
THE LANDSCAPE.
BUILT IN THE MIDDLE AGES
AS A PROVING GROUND FOR KNIGHTS,
IT HOUSES PRISONERS
WHO TOIL UNDERGROUND,
MINING COAL AS PENANCE
FOR THEIR CRIMES.
FISHING AND FARMING PROVIDE
SUSTENANCE AND COMMERCE ALIKE.
517 SOULS
CALL THE SLEEPY BURG THEIR HOME,
BUT HOW FEW SHALL REMAIN
WHEN THE CARNAGE IS DONE.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Zeppeli: HMM.
( Speedwagon sighs )
JoJo: FARMERS SEEING
TO THE HARVEST.
THUS FAR, ALL IS WELL.
HOWEVER, DIO LURKS IN
THE SHADOWS WAITING TO STRIKE.
‐ Zeppeli: POW.
‐ ( bones pop )
JoJo: WHAT HAPPENED?
Zeppeli: UH, WELL,
SPEEDWAGON HAS BEEN BEGGING ME
TO SHARE IN YOUR POWER.
I MEANT TO HELP HIM CREATE
JUST A LITTLE BIT OF HAMON,
AS I DID
THAT FIRST DAY WITH YOU.
IT SEEMS I WAS TOO ROUGH.
DID MY FINGER SLIP?
UN MIGLIAIO DI SCUSE,
MY DEAR SPEEDWAGON.
( Speedwagon groans )
IN ENGLISH, PLEASE.
( gasps )
JoJo: OUR CULPRIT IS A LAD,
IT WOULD SEEM.
Zeppeli: HIS CRIME
WAS WELL PLANNED.
I SALUTE THE BOY'S INGENUITY.
Speedwagon: HOW COME YOU TWO
ARE HEAPING PRAISE
ON THAT LITTLE IMP?
HE'S MAKING OFF WITH EVERY POUND
WE HAVE TO OUR NAMES!
OI! BRING IT BACK!
JoJo: YES, HE TOOK OUR MONEY,
BUT THINK HOW
HE MIGHT BE ABLE TO HELP.
Zeppeli: AGREED.
A GUIDE WHO KNOWS
THE LAY OF THE LAND
WOULD NOT BE UNWELCOME.
♪
HYAH.
( grunting )
Speedwagon: WHAT THE‐‐
HE'S WALKING ON IT!
( JoJo grunts )
Zeppeli: JOJO,
YOUR SHOES ARE GETTING WET.
TRY TO BOLSTER YOUR HAMON
FOR THE SAKE OF YOUR WARDROBE.
( JoJo breathes deeply )
( grunts )
Zeppeli: AHH.
THAT WAS A NICE DIMINUENDO.
YOUR OVERDRIVE PASSED THROUGH
THE ROCKS AS SMOOTH AS SILK.
JoJo: DO YOU THINK I STRUCK
THE RIGHT SPOT, BARON?
Zeppeli: NO, BUT A COUPLE OF
PACES TO THE LEFT SHOULD DO IT.
£2 SAYS I'M RIGHT.
Boy: HUH?
( yells )
WHY'D IT SHOCK ME?!
Zeppeli: MOLTO BENE.
Boy: HUH? WHAT HAPPENED?
WHO ARE YOU?
WHY ARE YOU HOLDING ME?
JoJo: LAD, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
THE FALL SHOULDN'T
HAVE HURT YOU THAT BADLY.
DID I USE TOO MUCH HAMON?
Zeppeli: I'D GUESS
WE WERE MEANT TO GIVE CHASE
WHEN HE TOOK OUR BAG.
LOOK AROUND.
( JoJo gasps )
THIS IS...
Speedwagon: A GRAVEYARD.
Zeppeli: IT'S NO ACCIDENT
THAT WE NOW FIND OURSELVES
HELD BY THESE RESTLESS CADAVERS,
MY FRIENDS.
OUR YOUNG THIEF,
HE WAS HYPNOTIZED
AND MADE TO LURE US HERE.
Speedwagon: THERE, JOJO!
IT'S HIM!
Zeppeli: HUH?
♪
Dio: THE SUN IS GONE.
YOU WILL NOT LIVE
TO SEE IT RISE ONCE MORE.
JoJo: DIO.
( zombies growling )
( boy gasps )
WHY ARE THEY CRAWLING OUT?
Speedwagon: I‐I'VE BEEN
TRYING TO STEEL MY SPINE
LEADING UP
TO THIS LITTLE T ÊTE‐ À‐T ÊTE,
BUT IT'S LIKE THE GRIM REAPER'S
BREATHING DOWN ME NECK.
I'M ALL A‐SWEAT.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FIND MY COURAGE
WHEN THAT MONSTER'S
STARING RIGHT AT US, HUH?
SIR JOESTAR LOVED HIM,
AND ALL HE GOT FOR HIS TROUBLES
WAS DEATH.
LISTEN, YOU.
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR IT.
Zeppeli: THIS IS DIO BRANDO.
HE AND HIS MINIONS
HAVE NO POWER TO ATTACK US
WHILE WE STAND IN THE DAYLIGHT,
BUT HERE IN A FIELD
OF DARKNESS AND CARRION,
HE THINKS US EASY PREY,
RIPE FOR THE TAKING
AT ANY MOMENT.
A CREATURE OF SUCH GUILE
MUST NOT HAVE THE MASK.
SOMEHOW, WE WILL PURGE THE WORLD
OF THIS EVIL.
( JoJo grunts )
( zombies growl )
Zeppeli: EVEN MOLDERING KNIGHTS
OBEY HIM!
JoJo: WHAT DO THEY
CALL YOU, LAD?
Poco: UH, POCO.
JoJo: WELL, POCO, HANG ON TIGHT.
IT'S TIME FOR US TO GO.
Zeppeli: JOJO, THIS WAY!
JoJo: LEAD ON.
( Zeppeli yells )
( JoJo inhales )
ZOOM PUNCH!
( bones pop )
( Poco gasps )
♪
Zeppeli: DIO BRANDO.
JOJO AND SPEEDWAGON
HAVE TOLD ME MUCH.
TO THE MASK THAT ALLOWS YOU
TO ACT OUT YOUR EVIL HEART,
I SAY ONLY THIS.
THIS TIME, I BREAK YOU.
( Dio hisses )
Zeppeli: HEY, BAMBINO,
IT'S EASY TO BE COCKY
WHEN YOU'RE UP THERE
OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
COME AND FIGHT.
Dio: YOU DARE
TO ADDRESS ME THUS, INSECT,
I, THE PINNACLE OF CREATION?
TO MERE HUMANS,
I AM LIKE UNTO A GOD,
SO WHY WOULD I CAVORT
DOWN IN THE FILTH WITH YOU?
( Zeppeli gasps )
HE ALMOST KNOCKED ME OFF MY FEET
WITH A BLAST OF PURE HATE.
ALREADY, THIS DIO
HAS THE SOUL OF A TYRANT.
Dio: ALL OF THE SCARS FROM
MY BATTLE WITH JOJO HAVE HEALED,
ALL SAVE THIS ONE.
COME, CHARLATAN.
RELINQUISH YOUR BLOOD,
THAT I MAY ERASE
THIS IMPERFECTION.
Zeppeli: TELL ME.
TO UNDO YOUR INJURIES,
HOW MANY INNOCENT LIVES
DID YOU CONSUME?
Dio: I DON'T KNOW.
HOW MANY LOAVES OF BREAD
HAVE YOU EATEN IN YOUR LIFETIME?
‐ ( Zeppeli grunts )
‐ JoJo: DIO!
( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Zeppeli: I WILL TAKE HIM.
( yells )
YOUR DOOM IS NIGH, DIO.
( both gasp )
Zeppeli: SOLAR HAMON,
PIERCE THE NIGHT!
SUNLIGHT YELLOW OVERDRIVE!
JoJo: HE DID IT. HIS HAMON
IS MOVING ITS WAY UP DIO'S ARM.
( Dio chuckles )
( Zeppeli gasps )
Dio: CONSIDER THIS AN ECLIPSE.
Zeppeli: UHH. YOUR HAND...
IT'S FREEZING ME.
( screams )
( gasping )
Dio: IT'S SIMPLE, REALLY.
FOR HAMON TO WORK,
BLOOD MUST FLOW THROUGH THIS ARM
WITH WHICH YOU HIT ME.
I FROZE THE VERY BLOOD
IN YOUR VEINS,
RENDERING
YOUR ATTACK POWERLESS.
I HAVE MASTERY OF MY BODY
IN WAYS THAT YOU
CAN'T EVEN BEGIN TO DREAM.
YOU SEE, I JUST VAPORIZED
THE MOISTURE IN MY LEFT ARM.
THE FORCE OF IT PULLED IN
ALL HEAT IN THE IMMEDIATE AREA,
FREEZING YOUR ARM
IN THE PROCESS.
AND NOW...
TIME FOR THE COUP DE GR ÂCE.
THIS PUNCH
IS GOING TO SHATTER YOUR ARM
AND YOUR SKULL
LIKE A WINDOWPANE!
♪
JoJo: THINK AGAIN.
I'M ENDING YOUR REIGN OF TERROR
HERE AND NOW!
( Dio sputters )
JoJo: YOUR BLOOD,
I CAN FEEL THE EVIL
COURSING THROUGH IT.
Dio: STOP IT. YOU'RE GOING
TO SET ME ALL A‐TREMBLE.
MASTERFUL BLOCK, BY THE BY.
FOR THE MOMENT,
YOUR MENTOR LIVES.
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU HAD IT IN YOU.
Zeppeli: JOJO!
( JoJo grunts )
Dio: THAT SAID, IF YOU
KEEP CUTTING IN LIKE THIS,
I'M LIABLE TO LOSE MY TEMPER.
‐ Zeppeli: JOJO, NOW!
‐ JoJo: BARON, NOW!
Dio: IT'S USELESS!
AS YOU CAN SEE,
BY FREEZING MY ARM,
YOUR PUNY ATTACK
HAD NOWHERE TO GO.
IF YOU THINK HAMON
WILL SAVE YOU,
YOU ARE SORELY MISTAKEN.
Zeppeli: HIS STRENGTH IS LIKE
NOTHING I'VE EVER WITNESSED.
THIS FIEND IS OUR EQUAL
MANY TIMES OVER.
WAIT. HE'S ABOUT TO FREEZE
JOJO'S ARM JUST LIKE MINE.
COME WHAT MAY,
I CAN'T LET HARM BEFALL THE LAD.
( ice tinkles )
( yells )
( Dio chuckles )
JoJo: BARON ZEPPELI!
( Dio grunts )
( Poco screams )
Speedwagon: COR,
THIS AIN'T HAPPENING!
HUH?
( JoJo winces )
MY HAND'S COLD AS ICE.
EVERY NERVE
IS CRYING OUT IN PAIN.
THE SKIN ON MY FINGERS
IS PEELING.
HE REMOVED THE MOISTURE.
Speedwagon: THE BARON'S ARM
IS IN A PRETTY BAD WAY.
GANGRENE WILL TAKE IT IF WE
DON'T GET THE BLOOD FLOWIN'.
JoJo: WHAT DO WE DO?
HAMON'S THE ONLY WEAPON
IN OUR ARSENAL.
HOW DO WE STAND AGAINST HIM?
Dio: SO ANEMIC,
THIS PARLOR TRICK OF YOURS.
YOU SHOULD SAVE YOUR BREATH.
( rumbling )
Speedwagon: HUH?
IS IT AN EARTHQUAKE?
Dio: YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED THAT AIR
FOR ALL THE SCREAMING
I HAVE IN STORE FOR YOU.
TARUKUS, BLUEFORD,
ARISE, AND FIGHT AT MY COMMAND!
LET THEIR CRIES
OF ANGUISH RESOUND
SO THAT ALL MAY KNOW MY GLORY!
( JoJo gasps )
♪
Speedwagon: WHERE'D HE
DIG UP THESE BRUISERS?
( Tarukus growls )
JoJo: POCO, GET TO SAFETY.
Poco: UH‐HUH.
Dio: THESE ARE KNIGHTS,
CASUALTIES OF QUEEN ELIZABETH'S
FATAL MACHINATIONS
IN THE MID‐1500s
AGAINST MARY, QUEEN OF SCOTLAND.
HEED ME WELL.
I FIND THESE HUMANS VEXING.
I ORDER YOU TO DESTROY THEM.
I CARE NOT HOW.
Speedwagon:
TELL ME I'M DREAMIN'.
THAT BIG ONE BROKE THE BOULDER
WITH A SINGLE FINGER.
( Zeppeli gasps )
THEY ARE WAITING FOR JOJO.
HE'S THEIR MAIN TARGET.
HE'S A WARRIOR, BUT HE
CAN'T HANDLE BOTH OF THEM.
IF ONLY MY BLOOD
WOULD START MOVING A LITTLE BIT.
Speedwagon: THEN WHAT, BARON?
Zeppeli: THEN I COULD HEAL
MY ARM A LITTLE WITH HAMON.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO THAW
THIS DAMNABLE THING IN TIME?
Speedwagon:
IF IT'S HEAT YOU NEED,
SPEEDWAGON'S FEELING
RIGHT CHARITABLE THIS EVENING.
Zeppeli: WHAT?
SO YOU HAVE A PLAN, THEN?
Speedwagon: IN A PINCH,
I FIGURE THIS'LL DO YOU!
Zeppeli: YOU SELFLESS IDIOT.
Speedwagon: HEARD THEY TREAT
FROSTBITE IN THE ARCTIC
BY CUTTIN' OPEN A SEAL AND
STICKING THE FROZEN HAND OR FOOT
INTO THE POOR BLIGHTER.
( Blueford grunts )
‐ JoJo: ZOOM PUNCH!
‐ ( bones pop )
Blueford: AYE, PEASANT.
GIVE ME YOUR BLOOD!
( JoJo gasps )
HIS HAIR,
HE'S USING IT TO FEED ON ME.
‐ ( Speedwagon groans )
‐ Zeppeli: SPEEDWAGON...
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
Speedwagon:
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
I'D BE BUGGERED BEFORE I
LET HARM COME TO YOU OR JOJO
WHILE I CAN LEND A HAND.
JoJo: IF HE CAN DRINK
MY BLOOD THROUGH THIS,
THEN PERHAPS IT WILL SERVE AS
A CONDUIT FOR MY HAMON AS WELL.
SUNLIGHT YELLOW OVERDRIVE!
( gasps ) NOTHING HAPPENED.
HAVE I ALREADY LOST
TOO MUCH VITALITY
TO MAKE MY HAMON EFFECTIVE?
Zeppeli: I MAY HAVE
SOLD YOU SHORT, AMICO.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD RUN
WHEN THINGS GOT TRULY DIRE.
MI DISPIACE.
Speedwagon: BARON,
IF WE LIVE THROUGH THIS,
YOU AND ME ARE RIGHT AS RAIN.
♪
( JoJo gasps )
( Zeppeli gasps )
I NEED TO GET MY ARM WORKING!
THERE'S NO WAY
HE CAN TAKE THEM ALONE!
Speedwagon:
EYEBALLIN' THAT SWORD
FREEZES ME UP
WORSE THAN YOU JUST DID.
JOJO'S WELL OVER SIX FEET TALL,
BUT NEXT TO THAT THING,
HE MIGHT AS WELL BE TOM THUMB.
LOOK AT THE FACE ON THAT ONE.
AND THAT ONE,
HE'S THE BLEEDIN' MINOTAUR.
I CAN READ PEOPLE LIKE A BOOK,
AND THESE TWO
ARE FULL OF STORIES
SPEEDWAGON DON'T WANNA HEAR,
THANK YOU KINDLY.
Dio: YOU SHOULD
BE HONORED TO PERISH
AT THE HANDS OF THESE MEN,
TARUKUS AND BLUEFORD.
BOW TO MY WILL,
O WARRIORS OF YORE.
Narrator:
IN THE MID‐16th CENTURY,
TWO WOMEN WAGED WAR
FOR THE CROWN OF ENGLAND,
THE CUNNING QUEEN ELIZABETH I,
A TUDOR,
AND THE BEAUTIFUL MARY STUART,
QUEEN OF SCOTS.
THE MOST STEADFAST
OF HER VASSALS
WERE THE GREAT KNIGHTS
TARUKUS AND BLUEFORD.
THEY HAD LOST THEIR FAMILIES.
WITHOUT A PURPOSE
TO CENTER THEM,
A RAISON D' ÊTRE,
THEY WERE ADRIFT.
THE DUTIFUL MAN SEEKS RESPITE
NOT IN THE VAGARIES OF ROMANCE,
BUT IN SOMETHING LARGER
AND INEFFABLE.
IN MARY, THEY FOUND JUST THAT.
THEY SWORE TO SERVE AND HONOR
THE YOUNG QUEEN,
EVEN AT THE COST
OF THEIR OWN LIVES.
BUT ONE DAY,
MARY'S HUSBAND, LORD DARNLEY,
WAS FOUND MURDERED.
SEEING A CHANCE TO STRIKE,
ELIZABETH BLAMED MARY
FOR DARNLEY'S DEATH.
THE PEOPLE TURNED AGAINST MARY.
SHE WAS CAUGHT AND IMPRISONED
IN A SERIES OF CASTLES.
TARUKUS AND BLUEFORD FOUGHT
LIKE LIONS TO FREE THEIR QUEEN.
SO FEARSOME WERE THEY,
ELIZABETH APPROACHED THEM
WITH A BARGAIN.
Elizabeth: SURRENDER, AND BRING
AN END TO THIS BLOODSHED.
GRANT US BUT THIS ONE THING,
AND WE WILL SPARE MARY'S LIFE.
Tarukus: IF OUR LIVES CAN BUY
THE QUEEN HER FREEDOM, I ACCEPT.
Blueford: I'VE NO REGRETS.
Narrator:
THEY WENT TO ELIZABETH
AND SEALED THEIR FATE.
( Tarukus growls )
( Blueford growls )
Executioner: YOU THINK
YOU'RE SO SELFLESS, DON'T YA?
WELL, YOU'RE LOSING
YOUR HEADS FOR NOTHING.
YOUR PRECIOUS MARY'S
ALREADY WORM FOOD.
GO AHEAD.
TAKE A LOOK OVER BY THAT WALL
IF YOU'RE HAVIN' YOUR DOUBTS.
NOT SO ROYAL NOW, IS SHE?
( both gasp )
( both scream )
Tarukus: ELIZABETH, YOU SERPENT!
YOU PLAYED US FALSE
AND MURDERED MARY ANYWAY!
Blueford: I DIE THIS DAY.
BUT MY HATRED FOR YOU
AND YOUR WRETCHED FAMILY
WILL LIVE FOREVER!
Both: CURSES ON YOU, QUEEN!
Narrator: AND THUS
THEY WENT TO THEIR END.
LEGEND HAS IT THAT TARUKUS'S
NECK WAS STIFF WITH FURY,
AND THE HEADSMAN
BROKE MANY AN AX
BEFORE THE TASK
WAS FINALLY DONE.
FOR HIS PART,
BLUEFORD'S HAIR COILED
AROUND THE EXECUTIONER'S FEET,
THE PEERLESS LOCKS
SLICING THE MAN'S FLESH.
Dio: THE STORY
OF THESE BRAVE KNIGHTS' BETRAYAL
SEEMS TO HAVE
STRUCK A CHORD WITH ME.
FROM THE EARTH, I CALLED THEM
TO WREAK THEIR VENGEANCE
ALL THESE CENTURIES LATER.
SUCH IS THE POWER AT MY COMMAND.
IN LIFE, THEY WERE FEARSOME.
IN DEATH, THEY ARE INVINCIBLE!
( Tarukus growls ) WE HAVE
SWORN FEALTY TO LORD DIO.
Blueford: WE HAVE COME
TO LAY WASTE TO THIS WORLD.
IT IS A PLACE
WITHOUT REDEMPTION.
( Speedwagon groans ) THAT HATE
THEY FELT WHEN THEY DIED,
IT HAD 300 YEARS TO FERMENT.
( both hiss )
Speedwagon: DIO'S TURNED
THE FLOWER OF KNIGHTHOOD
INTO VENGEFUL MONSTERS.
KEEP YOUR WITS ABOUT YOU, JOJO!
( JoJo exhales )
HAMON WITHIN ME, COME TO MY AID!
SCARLET OVERDRIVE!
‐ ( Blueford gasps )
‐ Zeppeli: LOOK AT THAT POWER.
Speedwagon: HUH?
HE LOOKS SO CALM,
BUT I KNOW THEY AIN'T FAR
FROM HIS THOUGHTS,
ALL THAT HE'S LOST
AND WHAT HE'S REDISCOVERED.
GODSPEED, YOU BRAVE BASTARD.
Blueford: METHINKS THIS BOY
IS A CHAMPION OF HIS DAY.
HE SHALL MAKE THE PERFECT TARGET
UPON WHICH TO PRACTICE
THE ART OF WAR.
( zombie roars )
THIS ONE'S FLESH BELONGS TO ME!
OH, YES. I CAN SMELL
HIS DELICIOUS CARTILAGE ALREADY.
JoJo: ANOTHER ZOMBIE?
Zombie: EH?
Blueford: HE IS OUR FOE.
GET THEE GONE FROM HERE,
YOU GLUTTON.
( nose sniffs )
( zombie yelps )
JoJo: HE MOVES
WITH INFERNAL SPEED.
Blueford: MILORD DIO,
IN THIS YOUNG MAN,
I DO SENSE
A GREAT RESERVOIR OF SPIRIT.
I HUMBLY PETITION YOU
FOR THE RIGHT
TO FACE HIM IN SOLE COMBAT
AND STRIKE HIM DOWN.
Dio: AS YOU WILL, THEN.
Blueford: TARUKUS,
THIS ONE HERE'S MINE.
Zeppeli: THAT'S BLUEFORD,
THE BLACK KNIGHT.
HE WAS KNOWN TO BE
A FLAWLESS FIGHTER,
AND HE WAS
UTTERLY DEVOID OF MERCY.
Speedwagon: JUST WATCHIN' HIM
PUT ONE FOOT
IN FRONT OF THE OTHER,
I CAN TELL
HE'S NO ONE TO TANGLE WITH.
JoJo: BACK IN MY SCHOOL DAYS,
WE LEARNED ABOUT THIS MAN,
HE AND TARUKUS,
AND NOW HE RETURNS
FROM THE DEAD TO KILL ME?
RELAX YOUR MUSCLES, JOJO.
BREATHE STEADILY,
NO MATTER WHAT!
( Blueford yells )
( JoJo gasps )
WHAT'S THIS?
HE'S GOT BOTH HANDS
BEHIND HIS BACK.
BLUEFORD IS GIVING NOTHING AWAY.
WHICH ONE IS HIS SWORD ARM?
Narrator: NEITHER.
HIS HAIR WIELDS THE BLADE.
JoJo: NO. BUT HOW‐‐
Blueford:
YOU'VE A KEEN EYE, MY BOY.
MY HAIR'S DANSE MACABRE
HAS CLAIMED MANY.
HAVE AT THEE!
( JoJo screams )
Speedwagon: JOJO!
♪
Zeppeli: OH, NO.
HE'S AT A SERIOUS DISADVANTAGE.
NO AIR TO BREATHE
MEANS NO HAMON.
Speedwagon: WE HAVE TO HELP HIM.
Zeppeli: WHAT? NOW THIS BRUTE?
Speedwagon: DAMN. HE NEEDS US,
AND WE CAN'T LIFT A FINGER
TO SAVE HIM.
( Dio chuckles )
JOJO'S AS GOOD AS DEAD.
HE CAN'T
TOUCH BLUEFORD UNDERWATER.
I WILL GO. HERE,
THERE IS NOTHING LEFT TO SEE.
AND NOW I WILL TRANSFORM
THIS SLEEPY VILLAGE
INTO A NECROPOLIS.
THE ZOMBIES I CREATE WILL
DEVOUR ENGLAND LIKE A PLAGUE,
WITH THE WORLD SOON TO FOLLOW.
♪
JoJo: I‐‐I NEED TO BREATHE.
I NEED TO GENERATE HAMON.
JUST A SINGLE BREATH.
Blueford: GO, BOY.
MAKE FOR THE SURFACE IF YOU CAN.
I SUFFER NOT FOR WANT OF AIR,
BUT MY ARMOR LEAVES ME SORELY
ENCUMBERED UNDER THE WATER.
A DUEL BETWEEN HEROES.
IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
YOU CAN BEAT ME TO THE TOP.
( JoJo gurgles )
Blueford: COME.
YOU'LL DROWN IF YOU TARRY.
ACT, AND QUICKLY!
JoJo: CAN I MAKE IT?
OR WILL I JUST
GET DRAGGED DOWN TO MY DOOM?
I GET ONE CHANCE.
( gurgles )
Narrator: AS DEATH READIED
HIMSELF FOR ANOTHER VICTIM,
JOJO FELT A WELLSPRING
OF RESOLVE BURST FORTH.
HIS LUNGS SCREAMING FOR BREATH,
AN ORDINARY MAN
WOULD MINDLESSLY CLAW HIS WAY
TOWARDS THE SURFACE,
BUT JOJO KNEW BETTER THAN THAT.
INSTEAD HE TURNED AND SWAM DOWN,
DEEPER INTO THE ABYSS.
Blueford: HE'S MAD.
HE'S GOING DEEPER DOWN.
George: WHAT'S THIS?
AND WON'T GIVE IT BACK?
YOU'RE TRYING
TO TAKE IT AWAY FROM HIM.
THAT'S THE REASON.
CHANGE YOUR STRATEGY.
TRY GIVING IT TO HIM INSTEAD.
JoJo: WIND KNIGHTS LOT,
IT'S A COAL‐MINING TOWN.
THAT MEANS COLLAPSED TUNNELS
AND SUNKEN EARTH.
( gasps ) THERE!
IF I'M RIGHT,
THERE SHOULD BE AIR
TRAPPED
UNDERNEATH THESE ROCKS.
I FOUND IT.
WITH JUST ONE BREATH,
MY BLOOD IS
GENERATING HAMON AGAIN.
Blueford: THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
JoJo: PREPARE YOURSELF,
SERVANT OF EVIL.
THE TABLES HAVE TURNED.
DOWN HERE, MY HAMON
WILL HIT YOU ALL THE HARDER.
UNDERWATER
TURQUOISE BLUE OVERDRIVE!
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ WITH YOU
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
( vocalizing )
♪
Speedwagon:
BLUEFORD IS A MESS!
Tarukus: I JUST HIT 'EM
UNTIL THEY FALL TO PIECES.
Blueford: THIS PAIN IS NOTHING!
Man: THE DAY WILL COME WHEN THIS
WILL BE THE DEATH OF YOU.
JoJo and Zeppeli:
LIFE MAGNETISM OVERDRIVE!