♪
( all yell, gasp )
Von Stroheim: THIS‐‐
THIS CAN'T BE!
( man vocalizing )
( Von Stroheim stammering )
I DIDN'T SEE HIM WITH THE MASK.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT HE HAD IT
ANYWHERE NEAR HIM.
I DIDN'T SEE HIM
PUT IN THE RED STONE.
Speedwagon: NO, IT CAN'T BE.
DEAR GOD.
JoJo: KARS.
♪
Singer: ♪ COME ON
( men vocalizing )
( JoJo gasps )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( JoJo sputtering )
( Speedwagon and Smokey gasp )
( men murmuring, shuddering )
Soldier:
HE STOOD UP AGAIN, MAJOR.
Von Stroheim: EHH.
YOU'RE THE FATHERLAND'S
CREAM OF THE CROP.
HE HAS BECOME THE UBERMENSCH.
CAN IT BE?
I THOUGHT NO CREATURE COULD
ATTAIN PERFECTION, BUT NOW...
JoJo: DAMN YOU.
Von Stroheim: SEE THAT,
HOW HIS ARM IS BURNING?
MAYBE WE DON'T HAVE
TO FIGHT PERFECTION AFTER ALL.
HAMON MELTS HIS ACCURSED FLESH
EVEN NOW.
IN ANOTHER MINUTE, THERE WILL
BE NOTHING LEFT OF HIM.
HE HAS LUSTED AFTER
THE RED STONE FOR MILLENNIA,
BUT WHEN IT IS
ALL SAID AND DONE,
HIS QUEST FOR IMMORTALITY
HAS FAILED!
YOU WILL PERISH
KNOWING THAT YOU ARE A FAILURE!
( men murmur )
Von Stroheim:
READY THE U. V. AMPLIFIER
FOR ANOTHER SHOT.
ONE DIRECT HIT SHOULD BE
ENOUGH TO FINISH HIM OFF.
HURRY IT UP, SOLDIER.
German: JAWOHL.
♪
( Smokey gasps )
WHAT'S HE DOING?
LOOKS LIKE HE'S THINKING.
( owl hoots )
Speedwagon:
STARING AT A DAMN SQUIRREL.
WHAT THE HELL?
Smokey: LOOK! MR. SPEEDWAGON!
HIS HAND, IT'S CHANGING.
JoJo: I'VE SEEN
SOME CRAZY STUFF, BUT THIS?
( squirrel chitters )
Speedwagon: GETS HIS HANDS
ON THE RED STONE,
FIRST THING HE DOES
IS MAKE A SQUIRREL?
Smokey: OH, HEY.
WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
I THINK IT FOUND A FRIEND.
JoJo: HEY, SQUIRREL,
GET AWAY FROM THAT THING!
YOU DON'T KNOW
THE GUY IT'S MADE OF.
( all gasp )
( squirrel roars )
( all yell )
( Von Stroheim yells )
SQUIRREL INCOMING!
( soldier gagging )
JoJo: SOLDIERS, FULL RETREAT!
( soldier #2 screams )
♪
Speedwagon: MY GOD.
HE HAS COMPLETE MASTERY
OVER ORGANIC LIFE.
Kars: HUH.
( Von Stroheim sighs )
Smokey: ALL RIGHT.
( Speedwagon sighs )
Smokey: THE SUN IS RISING.
( vampires screaming )
Speedwagon:
NOT A ONE OF 'EM LEFT ALIVE.
KARS IS ABOUT TO GET
WHAT'S COMING TO HIM.
THANK GOODNESS.
( JoJo gasps )
( woman vocalizing )
♪
HOW...
Smokey: THINK AGAIN.
HE'S FEELING FINE.
Speedwagon: HE'S STANDING
IN THE MORNING SUN,
AND HE COULDN'T
CARE LESS ABOUT IT.
( Kars chuckles )
( laughing )
Speedwagon: JOJO,
THIS IS A HORRIBLE NIGHTMARE.
WE'RE DOOMED.
THIS IS THE DAY ALL OF US DIE.
HUMANITY'S DONE FOR.
( Kars laughs )
ALPHA AND OMEGA BOTH,
I AM THE PINNACLE OF ALL LIFE
THAT HAS EVER TROD THE EARTH.
ALL OF THEIR FORMS
ARE MINE TO TAKE,
AND YOU, MY OLD NEMESIS,
I SEE HOW ENTRANCING YOU ARE.
YOURS IS A BEAUTY THE LIKES
OF WHICH I HAVE NEVER SEEN.
I ONCE FEARED YOU,
BUT NOW I FEAR YOU NO MORE.
( laughs )
Speedwagon: KARS,
HE'S BECOME INVINCIBLE.
HE HAS NO WEAKNESSES NOW.
HE EVEN SHRUGS OFF HAMON
LIKE IT'S NOTHING.
HE'S WON, AND HE KNOWS IT.
YOU CAN SEE IT IN HIS EYES.
KARS THE PILLAR MAN IS NO MORE.
HE'S BECOME KARS,
THE ULTIMATE CREATION!
Von Stroheim:
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I'M THE ONE
WHO HIT HIM WITH U. V.
AFTER HE PUT ON
THE COMPLETED MASK.
Smokey: IS‐‐IS THERE
REALLY NO WAY
TO STOP HIM, MR. SPEEDWAGON?
HE'S SO STRONG NOW.
WE'RE ALL GONNA BE FOOD
FOR THIS WALKING MUSEUM PIECE.
( Kars chuckles )
( JoJo grunts )
NO. I'VE GOT A PLAN.
( all gasp )
Speedwagon: DID I
HEAR YOU RIGHT, JOJO?
JoJo: HOLD HER. UH‐HUH.
ONE LAST ALL‐OR‐NOTHING GAMBIT.
Von Stroheim: "ALL‐OR‐NOTHING
GAMBIT," YOU SAY?
JoJo: YEAH. IT'S MY FINAL MOVE.
Von Stroheim:
WHAT DOES IT INVOLVE?
Smokey: JOJO,
WHEN YOU SAY, "FINAL MOVE,"
YOU'RE NOT REFERRING
TO THAT FINAL MOVE, ARE YOU?
JoJo: LISTEN UP.
THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO DO FOR YOURSELF.
Von Stroheim:
JUST TELL ME WHAT TO DO,
AND I'LL FOLLOW
YOUR LEAD, JOJO.
JoJo: HUMPH.
( chuckles )
RUN FOR YOUR LIFE!
Smokey: AWW, MAN!
I KNEW YOU WERE GONNA DO THAT!
( Kars shrieks )
HAMON USERS MEAN
NOTHING TO ME NOW,
BUT YOU ARE A SPECIAL CASE.
THIS IS A HISTORIC MOMENT,
AND WAMUU AND ESIDISI
MUST BE AVENGED.
I SHALL CELEBRATE MY REBIRTH
WITH THE UTTER ERADICATION
OF JOSEPH JOESTAR.
( Smokey gasping )
HE'S GAINING ON US!
JoJo: NOT HELPING!
REALLY, HOW AM I GONNA THINK OF
SOMETHING WITH YOU CARRYING ON?
WE'VE STILL GOT
OUR DIGNITY, SMOKEY.
Speedwagon: JOJO'S OUT THERE
RISKING LIFE AND LIMB
TO LEAD KARS AWAY FROM US.
GOOD ON YA.
BUT STILL,
IT IS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
THIS FOE AIN'T ONE YOU CAN BEAT.
Smokey: HE'S COMING.
IF YOU'RE GONNA THINK
OF SOMETHING, DO IT NOW!
JoJo: WHY ARE YOU
RUNNING WITH ME, ANYWAY?
MAYBE YOU HAVEN'T
NOTICED THIS YET, SMOKEY,
BUT I'M THE ONE WHO'S GOT KARS
REALLY BENT OUT OF SHAPE,
YOU KNOW.
YOU AND I ARE GOOD FRIENDS,
SO I'LL TAKE IT REALLY BADLY
IF YOU DIE BECAUSE OF ME TODAY.
FOR THE MOMENT, AT LEAST,
KARS IS AFTER MY BLOOD ALONE.
HE THINKS
THAT KILLING ME'S A GOOD WAY
TO RING IN HIS NEW LIFE,
WHICH MEANS THAT MONSTER'S
NOT GONNA STOP CHASING ME
UNTIL I'VE DRAWN
MY FINAL BREATH.
Smokey: JOJO...
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU REALLY NEED TO KNOW.
LISA LISA, SHE'S MORE
THAN JUST SOME HAMON MASTER.
‐ SHE'S YOUR‐‐
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
THAT WAS FAST.
QUIT FLAPPING,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
Von Stroheim:
SPEEDWAGON, TELL ME,
HAS THAT PILLAR MAN
REALLY BECOME THE PERFECT BEING?
Speedwagon: YES.
OUR GREATEST FEAR
HAS BEEN REALIZED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF US.
KARS HAS BECOME
AN UNSTOPPABLE FORCE OF NATURE.
Narrator: A PERFECT BEING IS,
ABOVE ALL, INVINCIBLE.
THAT MEANS IT DOES NOT GROW OLD.
IT WILL NEVER SUCCUMB
TO DEATH IN ANY FORM.
ADDITIONALLY,
IT HAS THE ABILITIES
OF ALL OTHER LIFE‐FORMS
AT ITS DISPOSAL
AND OUTPERFORMS THEM.
AND FINALLY,
ITS PREDOMINANT FORM
IS THE STANDARD BY WHICH
PHYSICAL PERFECTION IS JUDGED.
Speedwagon: UHH.
WE HAVE NO WAY TO STOP HIM NOW.
WE'VE ALREADY LOST.
HE HAS NO WEAKNESSES AT ALL.
HUMANS CAN'T KILL HIM.
NOT EVEN HAMON
OR THE SUN ITSELF
WILL DO A LICK OF GOOD
AGAINST HIM.
( shudders ) JOJO!
JoJo: SORRY, BUT YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO TELL ME LATER.
Smokey: HUH?
JoJo: I'M KINDA SHORT ON TIME.
Smokey: JOJO!
♪
( Kars scoffs )
THAT WON'T SAVE YOU.
( grunts )
JoJo: HAH HAH!
YOU'RE NOT
THE ONLY ONE WITH WINGS.
I'M COMING FOR YA!
♪
Speedwagon: UP THERE. THAT'S‐‐
Von Stroheim:
ONE OF OUR GERMAN WARPLANES.
( yells )
( Speedwagon coughs )
JOJO!
( chuckles )
( Kars growls )
♪
Narrator:
KARS MUTATES HIS FEATHERS
INTO PLATED PROJECTILES
AS HARD AS ARMADILLO SHELLS
AND COATS THEM
WITH A BULLET‐DEFLECTING OIL.
THEREFORE, THEIR TOUGHNESS
MAKES THEM IDEAL
NOT ONLY AS SHIELDING,
BUT AS WEAPONS
IN THEIR OWN RIGHT.
JoJo: SHOOTING THOSE FEATHERS
AT ME IS DIRTY POOL.
( gasps )
THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
TOUCHING DOWN IS NOT AN OPTION.
I'VE GOT TO MAKE MY GETAWAY!
( Kars scoffs )
Smokey: JOJO!
AW, MAN, HOW LONG CAN HE LAST
WHEN ALL HE CAN DO
IS RUN FOR IT?
Speedwagon: FLY, BOY,
AND DON'T LOOK BACK.
THAT'S ALL WE HUMANS CAN DO NOW,
JUST TRY TO SAVE OUR SKINS.
JoJo: 240 KILOMETERS AN HOUR.
( sighs )
I DON'T CARE HOW PERFECT
THAT BASTARD MAY BE.
THIS PLANE
HAS GOT MORE HORSEPOWER.
I'M SAFE FOR NOW.
IF HE HAS ANY MORNING PLANS,
HE'D BETTER CANCEL 'EM,
BECAUSE I'M IN THIS
FOR THE LONG HAUL.
( gasps ) OR AM I?
TWO HOURS LEFT.
GUESS I CAN'T GIVE HIM THE SLIP
FOR AS LONG AS I HAD THOUGHT.
Kars: YOU CRETIN.
THAT METAL COFFIN OF YOURS
WILL ONLY PROTECT YOU
FOR SO LONG.
( laughs )
IF YOUR PLAN
INVOLVES LANDING SOMEWHERE,
I'VE GOT NEWS FOR YOU.
THE ONLY WAY
YOU'LL RETURN TO TERRA FIRMA
IS IN BLOODY CHUNKS.
Speedwagon: JOJO.
JOJO, DO YOU READ ME?
THIS IS SPEEDWAGON. OVER.
JoJo: HEY. YOU GUYS
MISSING ME DOWN THERE YET?
( Speedwagon sighs )
THANK GOODNESS.
LISTEN, YOU WERE SMART
TO GRAB THAT PLANE.
I KNOW IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT THE GERMANS AND I
WILL DO WHAT WE CAN
TO HELP FROM HERE.
DO YOU HAVE A MAP?
JoJo: YEAH. FOUND IT.
Speedwagon: GOOD.
MAINTAIN RADIO CONTACT,
AND I'LL GUIDE YOU TO SAFETY.
( JoJo gasps )
JACKPOT.
Speedwagon: ALL RIGHT. FIRST
GIVE US YOUR CURRENT POSITION.
( static crackles )
Smokey: HUH?
Speedwagon: JOJO,
YOU'RE BREAKING UP.
‐ ( static crackles )
‐ WHAT'S GOING ON? HEY.
IF YOU CAN HEAR ME,
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, PIPE UP.
JoJo: YEAH. CLEAR AS A BELL.
HOW DO YOU THINK
THIS IS GONNA GO?
I MEAN, WE DON'T HAVE
A WEAPON OR FIGHTING TECHNIQUE
THAT'LL WORK ON KARS
WORTH A DAMN.
YOU WERE YELLING ABOUT HIM
BEING IMMORTAL, REMEMBER?
Speedwagon: DON'T I KNOW IT?
YOU RUNNING AWAY ISN'T IDEAL,
BUT IT'S ALL YOU CAN REALLY DO.
JoJo: HEH. MAYBE NOT.
LOOKING OVER THIS MAP
GAVE ME AN IDEA.
( Speedwagon gasps ) WHAT IDEA?
HEY, JOJO,
DON'T FACE KARS ALONE!
THIS IS NO TIME TO ACT THE HERO!
JoJo: HE'LL BE TOO STRONG LATER.
THIS IS THE ONLY TIME.
Speedwagon: DON'T DO IT!
I FORBID YOU TO GET YOURSELF
KILLED OUT THERE.
DO YOU HEAR ME?!
JoJo: JUST LISTEN FOR A SECOND.
I KNOW KARS IS THE MOST POWERFUL
CREATURE ON EARTH AT THE MOMENT,
BUT HE WAS BORN HERE.
THOUSANDS OF YEARS AGO,
THIS PLANET GAVE HIM LIFE,
AND IF WE'RE LUCKY,
IT'LL TAKE THAT LIFE RIGHT BACK.
Speedwagon: TAKE IT? BUT HOW?
WHAT IN THE WORLD DO YOU THINK
WILL BE A THREAT TO KARS?
JoJo: MAGMA.
AFTER ALL, MAGMA'S
THE HOTTEST SUBSTANCE ON EARTH.
I'LL DRIVE HIM INTO THE LAVA
AT ISOLA DI VULCANO.
EVEN HE CAN'T SURVIVE THAT.
Speedwagon: NO! YOU CAN'T!
YOU'VE RISKED YOUR NECK FOR
HUMANITY MORE THAN ENOUGH, BOY!
LET ME AND THE GERMANS
DO THE HEAVY LIFTING FOR ONCE!
Smokey: LISTEN TO HIM, JOJO.
DON'T BE STUPID!
KARS IS GONNA KILL YOU!
JoJo: MAYBE,
BUT I'M AT THE VOLCANO,
SO IT'S TOO LATE.
CARPE DIEM, AS THEY SAY.
Smokey: MR. SPEEDWAGON.
( Speedwagon shudders )
NO, GOD. NOT AGAIN.
LORD JOESTAR, HIS SON JONATHAN,
AND HIS SON GEORGE.
THE MEN OF THE JOESTAR FAMILY
WERE ALL CUT DOWN FAR TOO SOON.
♪
NOT AGAIN!
WHY DO THEY ALWAYS
HAVE THEIR LIVES TAKEN?!
DON'T FLY INTO THAT VOLCANO.
SURVIVE, FOR LISA LISA'S SAKE.
JoJo: HUH?
Speedwagon: LISTEN TO ME.
LISA LISA IS YOUR MOTHER.
JoJo: WHAT DID YOU SAY?
YOU'RE BREAKING UP.
‐ HUH?
‐ ( metal scraping )
THAT SOUNDS LIKE CHEWING.
( screams )
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?! YAAH!
PIRANHAS, HUH? THAT'S LOGICAL.
( gasps ) THEY'LL EAT THE PLANE
RIGHT OUT FROM UNDER ME.
BUT HOW'D THEY GET HERE?
( gasps )
THOSE FEATHERS KARS SHOT BEFORE,
THEY TURNED INTO
THESE DAMN THINGS.
( groans )
BUGGER ALL.
NO, DON'T EAT THE PARACHUTE!
YOU DEVIL‐FISH!
EH?
HUH?
OH, THIS IS BAD.
♪
YAAH!
( screams )
Speedwagon: JOJO!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CAN YOU EVEN HEAR ME?!
Smokey: JOJO!
Speedwagon:
PLEASE, SAY SOMETHING.
♪
( Kars laughs )
WHAT A MORON.
YOU THINK THAT PARACHUTE
IS YOUR SALVATION,
BUT ALL IT DOES
IS SEAL YOUR FATE.
YOU'RE JUST A BUTTERFLY
CAUGHT IN A SPIDER'S WEB.
( laughs )
NOW, JOJO,
TIME TO SPLIT YOU ASUNDER!
HUH? WHAT THE‐‐
BUT IF THIS IS A DECOY...
( gasps )
JoJo: HEY, KARS,
I'M A JOESTAR.
WE DON'T GO DOWN
WITHOUT A FIGHT!
YOU AND I HAVE GOT
A DATE WITH THAT VOLCANO!
DON'T TRY TO WEASEL OUT!
Both: JOJO!
‐ ( Kars screams )
‐ ( JoJo yelling )
Kars: DAMN YOU!
( grunts ) YOU'RE A LUNATIC.
♪
JoJo: GRANNY ERINA,
A LONG TIME AGO,
YOU TOLD ME
ABOUT MY GRANDFATHER.
YOU SAID HE DIED ON THE ATLANTIC
TO SAVE YOU AND FATHER
FROM HIS GREATEST FOE.
TRUST ME.
I DON'T MEAN TO BE A COPYCAT.
MAYBE THIS IS THE HAND
MY BLOOD DEALT ME.
( Kars grunts )
REALLY NOW. DO YOU THINK
I CAN'T PRY MYSELF
FROM THIS FOUL CONTRAPTION
BEFORE YOU TRY TO SMASH IT
INTO THE GROUND,
YOU GIBBERING PRIMATE?
( JoJo growls ) YOU COWARD!
( Kars chuckles )
KNOW THAT YOUR DEATH
WON'T ACCOMPLISH ANYTHING!
( JoJo gasps )
( Kars chuckles )
( yells )
( hand whirs )
Kars: IS‐‐IS THAT A HAND?
( men's chorus singing )
Von Stroheim: WHAT A SHAME.
ALL OF YOUR SCHEMING,
UND STILL YOU DIE HERE.
Kars: DAMN YOU.
JoJo: VON STROHEIM.
( sighs )
HOW DID YOU GET INTO THE PLANE?
WHEN DID YOU HAVE TIME?
( Von Stroheim chuckles )
I WASN'T SURE YOU COULD
HANDLE THIS BATTLE ALL ALONE.
NEXT TIME, I SHOULD STOW AWAY
IN THE CABIN PROPER.
( JoJo laughs )
NEXT TIME, HUH?
Von Stroheim: WHEN I GIVE
THE WORD, JUMP OUT, JOJO!
JoJo: NOT ON YOUR LIFE. NO WAY.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
PIRANHAS ATE MY DAMN PARACHUTE.
Von Stroheim:
UNLESS YOU WANT TO DIE,
JUMP OUT OF THERE THIS INSTANT!
( JoJo screams )
( static crackling )
Speedwagon: PLEASE RESPOND.
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU SAY!
TELL A BAD JOKE,
OR CALL ME AN OLD MAN.
LET ME HEAR YOUR VOICE
ONE MORE TIME.
Smokey: JOJO.
( both yell )
( both groaning )
JoJo: STROHEIM, YOU'RE CRAZY.
I'M CRAZY, TOO, BUT I ADMIT
WHEN SOMEONE'S GOT ME BEAT.
THAT WAS
A PRETTY COURAGEOUS MOVE.
Von Stroheim:
YOU SEEM TO BE ALL RIGHT,
BUT WHAT ABOUT‐‐WHERE'D HE GO?
PLEASE TELL ME
KARS FELL INTO THE LAVA.
‐ ( rumbling )
‐ EH?
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ ( Von Stroheim yells )
Kars: I'M...
STILL ALIVE...
WORMS!
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ WITH YOU
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
( vocalizing )
♪
Kars: DID YOU SAY,
"HAMON OVERDRIVE"?
JoJo: WHO'S LAUGHING NOW, HUH?
Kars: TO PURGE YOUR FEARS
AND REIGN FOREVER AS GODS!
Von Stroheim: JOJO!
JoJo: EVERYONE, GOODBYE.