Narrator: THIS GOTHIC STRUCTURE
BEGAN ITS LIFE
AS A 14th‐CENTURY CASTLE.
CONVERTED INTO A HOTEL
IN THE EARLY 1900s,
IT CLOSED 10 YEARS AGO
WHEN THE OWNER DIED.
NOW KARS IS USING
THE ANCIENT BUILDING
AS A SHELTER FROM THE SUN.
HE LURKS WITHIN WAITING.
ALAS, JOJO AND LISA LISA KNOW
NOTHING OF THE HOTEL'S LAYOUT.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
JoJo: DISGUSTING.
COME ON. COBWEBBY HALLS, REALLY?
WOULD IT KILL YOU
TO SWEEP A BIT?
OKAY, I GET IT. SCARY MONSTERS
DON'T DO MUCH HOUSECLEANING,
BUT THAT DOES LEAVE EVIDENCE.
SEE THIS BLOOD TRAIL?
IT SEEMS AS THOUGH WAMUU
TOOK A GOOD HAMON THRASHING.
CAESAR DIDN'T GO DOWN
WITHOUT GIVING
A GOOD ACCOUNT OF HIMSELF.
♪
WE MUSTN'T
LET WAMUU HEAL ANY MORE.
COACH LISA LISA,
IT'S TIME FOR SOME ACTION.
YUCK.
Lisa Lisa: WHAT IS IT?
JoJo: EH, IT'S JUST,
WELL, WHEN I TOOK AHOLD
OF THIS DOORKNOB,
IT WASN'T PLEASANT.
IT FELT LIKE I WAS
GRABBING THE HAND
OF SOMETHING COLD AND DEAD.
( male voice )
I'M NOT A DOOR.
JoJo: WHERE'S THAT‐‐( gasps )
Male: WHY ARE YOU
LOOKING AROUND?
‐ I'M NOT A DOOR, BUT I AM HERE.
‐ JoJo: WHA?
( creature wails )
JoJo: THAT'S‐‐IT'S A‐‐
Lisa Lisa: A VAMPIRE.
CAREFUL, JOJO!
‐ ( JoJo grunts )
‐ Lisa Lisa: JOJO!
( vampire laughs )
IF IT WEREN'T
FOR YOUR LITTLE YO‐YO THERE,
I WOULD HAVE PEELED YOUR FACE
RIGHT OFF YOUR HEAD.
( laughs ) HI. I'M WIRED BECK,
AND I'LL BE SLAYING YOU NOW.
I KILLED MY SWEETHEART, BUT THEN
I BUSTED OUT OF PRISON.
IN NO TIME,
LORD KARS TOOK ME IN
AND MADE ME
PART OF HIS LITTLE GANG.
HE'S GOT MY LOYALTY,
AND I AM NOT GOING
TO LET YOU GO IN THERE
AND DISTURB LORD KARS
WHEN HE'S ENJOYING
A WELL‐DESERVED REST.
JoJo: SO THEY'VE DONE IT.
IT'S BEGUN.
THEY'VE STARTED UNLEASHING
THEIR DEMON HOUNDS
ON THE WEAK AND INNOCENT.
( Beck humming and grunting )
JoJo: STOP THAT NOISE.
YOU'RE JUST ANOTHER VAMPIRE
WHO'S BOUND FOR HELL
AND LEAVING NOW.
WELL, THEN,
LET ME HELP YOU PLAN YOUR TRIP
SO YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WAIT ANY LONGER.
HUH? LISA LISA?
( Beck chuckles )
MMM.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL, MAGNIFICENT.
YOUR SKIN IS SO SOFT,
HEAVENLY, AND CLEAR.
LET ME HOLD YOU,
AND THEN I'LL DRINK YOUR LIFE
RIGHT THROUGH THAT SKIN.
Lisa Lisa: YOU'RE REALLY
NOT IMPRESSING ME.
I REFUSE TO WASTE
MY TIME LISTENING
TO YOUR WEAK FLIRTATIONS
AND SHALLOW THREATS,
BUT IF YOU WANT TO HOLD ME,
GO AHEAD, AND GIVE IT A TRY.
I GUARANTEE IT'LL BE
THE LAST THING THAT YOU DO.
( Beck growls )
( cackles )
JoJo: SPIKES!
HE'S COVERED TOP TO BOTTOM.
THEY'RE POPPING OUT OF HIM LIKE
HUNDREDS OF POINTED FINGERS.
THEY'RE METALLIC AND RAZOR SHARP
LIKE AN IRON‐MAIDEN JACKET.
Beck: I DON'T APPRECIATE IT
WHEN STUCK‐UP FEMALES
ARE INSULTING LIKE THAT.
THEY NEED TO BE PUNISHED.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
♪
I'LL GIVE YOU A NICE SQUEEZE.
I'M GOING TO HUG YOU TO DEATH!
JoJo: OH, NO. HE'S A LOT FASTER
THAN I THOUGHT HE WAS.
WAIT. I SEE. HER SCARF
BECOMES A HAMON‐FILLED WEAPON
WITH INCREDIBLY LONG REACH.
Beck: HUH?
GOSH, THANKS FOR THE THOUGHT.
YAH HAH!
YOU CAN'T CATCH ME LIKE THAT.
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
HEE HEE HEE!
SEE? I'M FREE.
( cloth rips )
Beck: HMM? THAT'S ALL?
WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
Lisa Lisa: COME, JOJO. LET'S GO.
JoJo: UH, OKAY.
LISA LISA'S MOVEMENTS,
THEY'RE EFFORTLESS
AND FLOW LIKE SILK, EFFICIENT.
SHE DOESN'T WASTE ANY ENERGY.
Beck: COME BACK!
YOU CAN'T JUST WALK AWAY.
HEY, YOU, WOULDN'T YOU AGREE
THAT A WOMAN
WHO BEHAVES LIKE THAT
NEEDS TO BE PUNISHED?
JoJo: OH, NO. YOU ARE
THE ONE BEING PUNISHED.
YOU SEE,
YOU'VE JUST RUN OUT OF TIME.
HAMON IS NOW RUNNING
ALL THROUGH YOUR BODY.
Beck: HUH?
( laughs )
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
I'M NOT‐‐
( screams )
NO!
♪
JoJo: LISA LISA HAS
REALLY GOT WHAT IT TAKES.
I THOUGHT SHE MIGHT BE
OUT OF HER DEPTH IN A FIGHT,
BUT IT'S PLAINLY OBVIOUS
SHE'S EVEN BETTER THAN ME.
I AM SO IMPRESSED.
I'M LUCKY TO HAVE HER
TRAINING ME.
‐ ( footsteps echoing )
‐ Lisa Lisa: BY THE WAY, JOJO,
HAVE YOU TAKEN IT? YOU REALLY
SHOULDN'T DELAY ANY LONGER.
YOU MUST USE THE ANTIDOTE.
JoJo: HUH? OH, YOU MEAN THIS?
Lisa Lisa: YES, OF COURSE.
JoJo: I'M GOING TO DRINK IT
ONLY AFTER I DEFEAT WAMUU.
HEH. SEE, THIS RING,
IT NO LONGER SIGNIFIES
A PROMISE BETWEEN ME AND WAMUU.
IT'S NOW A PROMISE
I MAKE TO CAESAR
THAT I WILL GO ON LIVING
AND STAY IN THE FIGHT.
WOULD YOU PLEASE HOLD IT FOR ME
UNTIL I ACTUALLY NEED IT,
LISA LISA?
Lisa Lisa: NO.
IT WOULD BE BETTER
IF IT STAYED WITH YOU.
WHO KNOWS
WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN TO ME?
JoJo: HUH?
♪
Narrator: AS THEY VENTURED
FURTHER INTO THE DEPTHS,
THE TRAIL OF BLOOD
GREW EVER THINNER.
BOTH JOJO AND LISA LISA
KNEW WELL
WHAT MEANING COULD BE DRAWN
FROM THAT FACT.
WAMUU'S HAMON WOUNDS
WERE HEALING.
♪
Wamuu: SO YOU'RE HERE.
I'VE BEEN WAITING.
I SEE YOUR POWERS
HAVE GROWN GREATLY.
BASTARD! YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO KILLED CAESAR.
NOW I‐‐
Lisa Lisa: COOL YOUR HEAD, JOJO.
NOW LOOK AT THE FLOOR.
JoJo: I'M VERY CALM.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M IN CONTROL HERE.
YOU MEAN THE FOOTPRINTS, RIGHT?
I NOTICED IT, TOO.
THERE ARE TWO SETS.
THAT MEANS KARS IS HERE!
TELL ME WHERE I CAN FIND HIM!
SHOW YOUR COWARDLY SELF NOW!
Lisa Lisa: INDEED. THERE ARE
TWO SETS OF FOOTPRINTS.
HE'S HERE,
BUT I FEEL DOZENS OF LUNGS
‐ MOVING THE AIR AROUND AS WELL.
‐ JoJo: EH?
Wamuu: SO IT'S YOU.
FASCINATING. YOU ARE EXTREMELY
COMPOSED AND PERCEPTIVE
THOUGH YOU ARE A WOMAN.
I CAN SEE HOW JOJO AND CAESAR
WERE ABLE TO LEARN
SO MUCH SO QUICKLY.
AND YOU CAN FEEL
EVEN THE LIGHTEST RESPIRATION.
YOU RANK
AMONG THE FINEST HAMON WARRIORS.
♪
JoJo: DAMN. LOOK AT THAT.
THERE'S SO MANY.
I'D GUESS YOU'RE ALL VAMPIRES.
IS THAT RIGHT?
NO RESPONSE? THAT'S CREEPY, TOO.
( gasps )
♪
KARS!
( Kars snaps fingers )
Vampire: LORD KARS SAW FIT
TO GIVE US, HIS CHOSEN ONES,
THE GIFT OF ETERNAL LIFE.
WE NUMBER 100.
ON OUR MASTER'S ORDER,
WE'LL TEAR YOU BOTH TO SHREDS,
100 AGAINST TWO, JOJO!
( vampires growling )
JoJo: YOU FIENDS.
( growling quiets )
♪
THIS REALLY IS NOT GOOD.
IT'S 100 OF THEM
AGAINST THE TWO OF US.
WE CAN'T WIN.
Wamuu: LORD KARS, A MOMENT.
BACK IN ROME, JOJO AND I
PROMISED TO FIGHT
ONE ANOTHER AGAIN.
I WANT REVENGE FOR ESIDISI.
PLEASE ALLOW ME
THE CHANCE TO FIGHT HIM.
Kars: NO. REMEMBER THAT MY GOAL
IS ONLY TO OBTAIN
THE RED STONE OF AJA.
Kars: DON'T FORGET THAT, WAMUU.
Wamuu: YES, LORD.
JoJo: OH, DARN, NO FIGHT.
WELL, I'M NOT
IN THE MOOD ANYWAY.
OF COURSE WE BOTH KNOW
I WOULD BEAT YOU.
BUT TO WHAT END?
ALL THESE VAMPIRES ARE HERE.
WHAT SORT OF MOTIVATION IS THAT,
I ASK YOU?
WIN OR LOSE, I WOULD STILL
COME OUT OF IT DEAD, RIGHT?
WITH ODDS LIKE THAT, GIVING UP
IS THE ONLY RATIONAL CHOICE,
SO I'M THROWING IN THE TOWEL.
DAMN. HAD TO TRY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS WORTH A SHOT,
EVEN IF YOU WERE WATCHING
ALL THE TIME.
A HAMON NET WAS A GOOD IDEA.
Kars: KILL THEM
WITHOUT ANY FURTHER DELAY.
Lisa Lisa: YOUR CHOICE,
BUT IF YOU KILL US,
YOU'LL NEVER GET THE STONE.
Kars: HMM? HOLD IT.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING NOW, WOMAN?
Lisa Lisa: YOU DON'T THINK
I'D HAVE THE STONE HERE WITH ME?
THAT WOULDN'T BE WISE,
NOW, WOULD IT?
WE'RE HEADED TO OUR DESTINATION.
IF WE'RE NOT THERE
IN TIME TO SET THE DEVICE,
THE RED STONE WILL BE DESTROYED,
AND YOU WILL HAVE NOTHING.
‐ Kars: HUH?
‐ Wamuu: HMM?
♪
( Kars chuckles )
LOOK, WOMAN,
DON'T TRY TO FOOL ME.
Lisa Lisa: ARE YOU CONFIDENT
THAT YOU AND YOUR MINIONS
WILL BE ABLE TO FIND IT IN TIME?
THE BOMB I SET
IS A VERY SMALL ONE,
BUT ENOUGH TO DAMAGE THE STONE
AND PREVENT ITS USE.
( Kars growls )
JoJo: COULD THIS REALLY BE TRUE?
SHE NEVER SAID ANYTHING.
WHATEVER. I'LL FOLLOW HER LEAD.
WERE YOU FELLOWS LISTENING?
IF WE DON'T STOP IT,
THE BOMB WILL GO BOOM.
Kars: EVEN IF TRUE, WE CANNOT
LET YOU LEAVE HERE ALIVE.
Lisa Lisa: THEREFORE,
I HAVE A SUGGESTION.
JOJO AND WAMUU CAN HAVE
THEIR FIGHT ONE‐ON‐ONE,
AND, KARS, YOU AND I
WILL ALSO FIGHT ONE‐ON‐ONE,
AND THOSE WHO ARE LEFT STANDING
WILL POSSESS THE STONE!
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
‐ Kars: WHAT?!
Lisa Lisa:
THE WINNERS OF THIS FIGHT
WILL HAVE THE RED STONE
AND ALL OF ITS POWER.
IT'LL BE MADE VERY CLEAR.
WHICH ONE OF US
WILL PROVE STRONG ENOUGH
TO WIELD THE STONE'S POWER?
WHO IS FIT TO SURVIVE?
THE PILLAR MEN OR HUMANKIND?
Kars: HOW DARE YOU SAY?
( Wamuu chuckles )
Kars: WAMUU.
Wamuu: LORD KARS,
THIS IS MOST ABSURD.
JoJo: SHE IS GOOD.
SHE'S JUST PROVEN HERSELF
TO BE A BETTER GAMBLER
THAN I COULD
EVER DREAM OF BEING.
( Kars chuckles )
NO DOUBT, YOU DO HAVE PLUCK.
VERY WELL. THEN WE WILL
BATTLE FOR THE STONE.
BUT DON'T GET COCKY.
YOU HAVE NO TOMORROW.
JoJo: USING ONLY WORDS,
SHE JUST TURNED A DIRE SITUATION
INTO MORE‐OR‐LESS EVEN ODDS.
THEN SO BE IT. LET'S DO THIS.
♪
( vampires laugh )
Kars: AND SO NOW
WE NEED TO ARRANGE
A TIME AND PLACE FOR OUR BATTLE.
WAMUU, WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
Wamuu: WE FIGHT TONIGHT
UNDER THE GAZE OF THE FULL MOON,
THE ARENA
AT THE BASE OF PIZ BERNINA,
15 KILOMETERS TO THE SOUTHEAST.
WE WILL MEET
AT THE SKELETON'S HEEL
STONE CIRCLE THERE.
MANY WARRIORS HAVE FOUND
DEATH, GLORY, OR BOTH
THROUGHOUT THE HISTORY
OF THAT PLACE.
Lisa Lisa: IN A STONE CIRCLE?
JoJo: HEY, YOU CAN'T
JUST CHOOSE A PLACE
BECAUSE IT HAPPENS TO SUIT YOU.
Kars: YES, WAMUU, I BELIEVE THAT
TO BE A FINE CHOICE.
NOW LET'S SPEAK
OF THE RED STONE.
JOJO, YOU WILL
BRING THE RED STONE OF AJA
TO THE SKELETON'S HEEL
AT MIDNIGHT TONIGHT.
AND DON'T FORGET
TO REMOVE THE BOMB.
THE WOMAN WILL REMAIN HERE
WITH US AS INSURANCE.
♪
( Wamuu grunts )
JoJo: WELL, LISA LISA?
Lisa Lisa:
THEY WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE DON'T RUN AWAY
FROM THE FIGHT.
IT IS A REASONABLE REQUEST.
JOJO, GO AND FETCH US
THE RED STONE.
YOU MUSTN'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
JoJo: WOULD I?
I'LL SEE YOU BACK AT THE ARENA.
TRUST ME, ALL RIGHT?
Lisa Lisa: I ASSURE YOU I DO.
( footsteps echoing )
♪
JoJo: CAESAR.
( gasps )
( footsteps crunching )
UNTIL YESTERDAY,
I LIVED MY LIFE
THINKING ONLY ABOUT MYSELF,
BUT NOW THERE'S
A NEW INTENSE FEELING
BURNING UP INSIDE OF ME.
IS THIS COMPASSION?
I SWEAR...
I JUST WANT TO DESTROY
THOSE BASTARDS
AND ALL THEIR LINE.
I HAVE TO DO IT
FOR CAESAR AND FOR MESHINA, TOO,
LISA LISA,
AND FOR EVERYONE ELSE I KNOW.
I'LL FIGHT FOR YOU ALL.
( case clatters )
( laughs )
OBVIOUSLY THERE'S NO BOMB HERE
OR ANYWHERE ELSE
FOR THAT MATTER.
LISA LISA,
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE UNDER PRESSURE
YOU ARE
ONE DECEPTIVE YOUNG WOMAN.
HMM.
WELL, NOW,
MAYBE I SHOULD BRING YOU
A CHANGE OF PANTIES
IN CASE YOU GET SCARED.
( laughs )
WAIT A MINUTE
WHAT ARE THESE PHOTOS?
WHAT? IT'S GRANNY ERINA.
WHAT WOULD LISA LISA
BE DOING WITH THIS?
HUH?
WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
"MAY 22, 1889"?
50 YEARS AGO.
THEN THAT YOUNG GUY THERE IS...
SPEEDWAGON!
AND GRANNY ERINA!
AND THAT'S STRAIZO
HOLDING A BABY.
LISA LISA, I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT YOUR PAST
OR THE LIFE YOU HAVE LED
OR WHO YOU'VE KNOWN.
WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY
BE DOING WITH THESE PHOTOS?
♪
( wind blowing )
( Wamuu chuckles )
Kars: IT'S GENUINE.
WE ACCEPT YOUR PROPOSAL.
WE HONOR YOU
BY FIGHTING ONE‐ON‐ONE.
Lisa Lisa: I SUPPOSE
THIS MEANS YOU SAW THE PHOTOS,
AND YOU'D LIKE
TO TALK ABOUT IT, RIGHT?
ACTUALLY I HAD INTENDED
TO DISCUSS THIS WITH YOU ANYWAY.
JoJo: START WITH WHO YOU ARE.
♪
Lisa Lisa: 50 YEARS AGO NOW,
ERINA LOST HER HUSBAND
ON A SHIP SAILING THE ATLANTIC.
HE WAS JONATHAN JOESTAR,
YOUR GRANDFATHER.
THAT HORRIBLE DAY,
YOUR GRANDMOTHER
SAVED THE LIFE OF A BABY GIRL.
THAT WAS ME.
I AM THE BABY
IN THAT PHOTOGRAPH.
JoJo: W‐WAIT A MOMENT HERE.
THAT WAS 50 YEARS AGO.
SO IF YOU WERE A BABY
50 YEARS AGO‐‐
HOLD ON NOW.
JUST HOW OLD ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
Y‐YOU'RE 50?!
( stammers )
OH, MAN. IF YOU'RE 50,
THAT MEANS THEN...
YOU'RE REALLY OLD!
( swallows )
IS THAT RIGHT? NORMALLY‐‐
Y‐YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
IN YOUR LATE 20s. HMM.
THEY SAY THAT HAMON ENERGY
IS LIFE ENERGY
AND KEEPS YOU YOUNG.
I GUESS THAT EXPLAINS
WHY YOU REALLY DON'T ACT
LIKE A YOUNG WOMAN
WOULD BEHAVE AT ALL.
AH. I THINK I SEE A LITTLE
WRINKLE BACK THERE. YUP.
( Lisa Lisa grunts )
JoJo: HEY, I'M JUST KIDDING,
ALL RIGHT?
Kars: VAMPIRES,
PREPARE THE ARENA.
LIGHT THE FIRES!
( vampires yelling )
Lisa Lisa: THERE IS NOT
ENOUGH TIME FOR US TO TALK NOW,
BUT WE REALLY DO NEED
TO FIND THE TIME,
BECAUSE OUR ROOTS
ARE DEEPLY CONNECTED.
JoJo: OUR ROOTS?
Lisa Lisa: THE STONE MASK
KILLED MY PARENTS.
ERINA WAS PREGNANT
WHEN SHE RESCUED
THE LITTLE GIRL ON THE SHIP.
SHE COULDN'T RAISE TWO CHILDREN,
SO STRAIZO
BECAME A FATHER TO ME.
( JoJo gasps )
STRAIZO AS A FATHER?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
Lisa Lisa: EVERYTHING I KNOW
ABOUT HAMON, STRAIZO TAUGHT ME.
HE EVEN GAVE ME
THE RED STONE OF AJA.
JoJo: HE DID THAT? WOW.
THIS IS ALL JUST SO UNBELIEVABLE
AND HARD TO ACCEPT.
Lisa Lisa:
IT'S TRAGIC BEYOND WORDS
THAT THE FEAR OF GROWING OLD
DROVE HIM TO COMMIT
SUCH ACTS OF MADNESS.
JOJO, MY FEELINGS
ABOUT YOU DEFEATING HIM
ARE EXTREMELY COMPLICATED,
BUT I BELIEVE
THAT IT WAS DESTINY.
JoJo: WHAT IS THERE TO SAY?
EVERYTHING, ALL OF IT,
IS SO COMPLICATED.
WHAT A BIZARRE RELATIONSHIP.
LISA LISA, SHE CARRIES WITH HER
A PAST PAINTED BY SADNESS.
‐ ( rumbling )
‐ Lisa Lisa: IT'S TIME.
THE REST OF IT
WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
JoJo: W‐WHAT'S
THAT RUMBLING NOISE?
( vampires gasping )
Kars: THEY HAVE COME.
IT WAS WORTH THE WAIT.
THE BATTLE CAN BEGIN NOW.
( vampires cheer )
Lisa Lisa: HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
( yelling )
Charioteer: OUT OF THE WAY!
I DON'T CARE
HOW MANY OF YOU GET CRUSHED!
JoJo: WHAT‐‐WHAT IS THAT THING,
A DINOSAUR?
NO, I THINK A HORSE.
THAT'S A HORSE.
Charioteer #2: LORD KARS,
LORD WAMUU, PLEASE MOVE!
THEY'VE GONE BERSERK!
I CAN'T CONTROL THEM!
( horses neigh )
Charioteer #2:
LORD WAMUU, PLEASE!
( Wamuu grunts )
AH, THESE ARE FINE STEEDS.
Kars: THE STONE MASKS
WORKED EXTREMELY WELL.
THEY'RE NOW STRONG VAMPIRES.
JoJo: WHA‐‐VAMPIRE HORSES?
♪
ON THAT TRACK, JOJO AND WAMUU
WILL FACE EACH OTHER ONE‐ON‐ONE
IN A FIERCE
ANCIENT‐STYLE CHARIOT DUEL.
( vampires cheer )
JoJo: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Charioteer #1: AN ANCIENT
ROMAN‐STYLE DEATH MATCH.
YOU WILL BATTLE,
RACING AROUND THE ARENA,
TRYING TO KILL EACH OTHER.
LORD WAMUU OR JOJO,
WHO WILL BE THE FIRST ONE
TO FALL UNDER THE WHEELS
OR GET BEATEN DOWN
BY HIS OPPONENT?
THE LOSER DIES!
Charioteer #2:
THOSE ARE THE RULES, JOJO.
THE BEASTS HAVE
A HUNDRED TIMES NORMAL STRENGTH.
EVEN LORD WAMUU
CAN BARELY CONTROL THEM.
JoJo: HOLD IT JUST A MINUTE.
I WILL FIGHT YOU ON ANY FIELD
OR IN ANY CAGE,
BUT VAMPIRES ARE YOUR MINIONS,
EVEN HORSES,
SO HOW IS THAT FAIR?
Kars: DON'T FRET, HUMAN.
THE REINS YOU USE
WILL CONDUCT HAMON.
WAMUU WILL USE
HIS SUPERIOR STRENGTH,
AND YOU CAN USE YOUR HAMON
TO CONTROL THEM.
JoJo: ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
THEY LOOK PRETTY VICIOUS.
BE CAREFUL. THEY'RE MEAN.
( horses neigh )
Lisa Lisa: THAT'S TRUE,
BUT A LITTLE HAMON DOES HELP.
‐ JoJo: AH.
‐ Vampires: WAMUU!
WAMUU! WAMUU! WAMUU!
WAMUU! WAMUU!
RAAH!
Kars: SEE WAMUU?
HE HAS CHOSEN AN ANCIENT FORM
FOR THIS BATTLE.
THAT'S A SIGN HE MEANS TO WIN.
IT'S NOT FOR FUN.
HE'S NOT GOING INTO THIS
FOR THE SPORT OF IT.
HE WANTS TO TAKE YOUR LIFE.
Lisa Lisa: JUST BEAT HIM, JOJO.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO WIN THIS.
THERE ARE NO DRAWS.
JoJo: WAMUU, HEY!
DID YOU NOTICE THAT I HAVEN'T
TAKEN THIS ANTIDOTE YET?
I MADE A PROMISE TO CAESAR
THAT I WOULDN'T DRINK THIS
UNTIL AFTER I TOOK YOU DOWN.
THAT PROMISE
IS GOING TO PROVIDE ME
WITH A POWER
I'VE NEVER EXPERIENCED BEFORE.
♪
WE'LL FACE THIS FIGHT
TOGETHER, CAESAR.
LET'S RIDE INTO BATTLE!
( horses neigh )
♪
♪ ALONG THE DRIFTING CLOUD
♪ THE EAGLE SEARCHING DOWN
ON THE LAND ♪
♪ CATCHING THE SWIRLING WIND
♪ THE SAILOR
SEES THE RIM OF THE LAND ♪
♪ THE EAGLE'S DANCING WINGS
♪ CREATE AS WEATHER
SPINS OUT OF HAND ♪
♪ GO CLOSER, HOLD THE LAND
♪ FEEL PARTLY NO MORE
THAN GRAINS OF SAND ♪
♪ WE STAND TO LOSE ALL TIME
♪ A THOUSAND ANSWERS BY
IN OUR HAND ♪
♪ NEXT TO YOUR DEEPER FEARS
♪ WE STAND SURROUNDED
BY A MILLION YEARS ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS WILL MAKE YOU
OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS WILL
MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪
Vampires: WAMUU! WAMUU! WAMUU!
WAMUU! WAMUU! WAMUU!
WAMUU! WAMUU!
Kars: BEGIN NOW!