♪
Narrator: THIS SENIOR GENTLEMAN
SEEMS FAMILIAR.
WE DEFINITELY KNOW
THAT UPRIGHT BEARING
AND THAT SCAR.
Man: IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, SPEEDWAGON.
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE
AN AMERICAN OIL TYCOON NOW.
Speedwagon:
THAT'S A BIT EXAGGERATED.
YOU LOOK AS YOUNG AS EVER,
STRAIZO.
HARD TO BELIEVE
WE'RE THE SAME AGE.
HAMON ENERGY IS LIFE ENERGY,
RIGHT? I ENVY YOU.
♪
Narrator: IT HAS BEEN
HALF A CENTURY
SINCE JONATHAN JOESTAR
MADE HIS SACRIFICE.
STRAIZO HAS SUCCEEDED
MASTER TONPETTY,
WHILE SPEEDWAGON HAS HAD SUCCESS
BUILDING A FORTUNE.
TOGETHER, THEY'RE HEADED
FOR MEXICO TO SEE SOMETHING.
THIS SOMETHING WAS DISCOVERED
BY A SPEEDWAGON‐FUNDED
EXPLORATION TEAM.
WHAT'S MORE
IS THAT IT'S A SECRET
KNOWN ONLY
TO THESE SELECT FEW.
Speedwagon: I TELL YOU, STRAIZO,
ONCE YOU LAY EYES ON THIS,
I BELIEVE‐‐NO, I AM CERTAIN
YOU'LL FEEL A CHILL.
IT'S FRIGHTFUL ENOUGH
TO MAKE EVEN YOUR
DISCIPLINED HAIR STAND ON END.
I FIND IT EVEN WORSE
THAN THE TERROR
WE FACED 50 YEARS AGO
WHEN WE ALL BATTLED WITH DIO.
( Straizo gasps )
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW LARGE THIS SPACE IS.
Speedwagon: AND THIS IS
THE REASON WE CAME HERE.
Straizo: WHAT? IT CAN'T BE!
A STONE MASK!
AND THERE ARE SO MANY OF THEM!
( gasps )
♪
Man: IT WAS IN THE FALL OF 1938.
I WAS DOING MY JOB,
JUST LIKE I ALWAYS DID,
EYES PEELED FOR A MARK.
Man #2: YOU GOTTA BE KIDDIN' ME.
Man #1: HUH?
Man #2: YOU REALLY NEVER HEARD
OF THIS FINE BEVERAGE?
ALL RIGHT. BY YOUR ACCENT,
I'D SAY YOU'RE IN FROM ENGLAND.
TOURIST, HUH?
( man #1 chuckles )
Vendor: NO KIDDIN'?
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE
THE BIG CITY YOUR HOME?
WELL, IF YOU WANT A DRINK,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO LAY DOWN SOME SHEKELS.
CASH IS THE KING AROUND HERE.
THE NERVE OF HIM!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LET
THAT MOOK STEAL YOUR WALLET.
GET AFTER HIM.
Thief: HAH!
WHAT A PATSY.
THAT WAS EASY AS PIE.
‐ ( gasps )
‐ ( officer laughs )
HEY‐A, SMOKEY.
LOOKS LIKE I FINALLY CAUGHT YOU
RED‐HANDED, YA PUNK.
( Smokey yells )
Officer: WHAT ARE YA DOIN'
ON MY BEAT, YOU TRASH?
( Smokey coughs )
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
THEY LOCK YOU UP
FOR 20 YEARS.
Smokey: TAKE IT EASY.
PLEASE, SIR.
I ONLY PINCHED A WALLET.
Officer: I HATE BOTTOM FEEDERS
LIKE YOU PREYIN' ON THE PUBLIC.
BUT SEE, I'M NICE.
I'LL DO YOU A SOLID.
I'M GONNA LET YOU
BRING ME $20 EVERY WEEK,
ALSO HALF
OF EVERYTHING YOU GLOM.
Englishman: HULLO.
Officer: HMM?
♪
HEY, IT'S THE PIGEON
WHAT GOT HIS WALLET LIFTED.
THIS IS EVIDENCE,
SO I'M GONNA BE KEEPIN' IT.
Englishman: WELL, NOW,
HOW SHALL I PUT THIS?
HERE IS WHAT HAPPENED.
THERE ACTUALLY IS NO CRIME
SINCE THAT WALLET
WAS A GIFT, CONSTABLE.
‐ Officer: HMM?
‐ Officer #2: HMM?
Smokey: EH?
( narrating )
FOR SOME REASON,
THIS SIX‐AND‐A‐HALF‐FOOT
GIANT OF AN ENGLISHMAN
WAS COVERING FOR ME.
Englishman: SO THEN, SIR,
WOULD YOU PLEASE RETURN
BOTH WALLET AND BOY?
Officer: WHAT'D YOU JUST SAY?
Englishman: AS I SAID,
IT WAS A GIFT.
HE AND I ARE GOOD FRIENDS.
LET HIM GO, PLEASE.
‐ ( Smokey grunts )
‐ Officer: UH‐HUH.
A GOOD FRIEND, EH?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHAT YOUR GOOD FRIEND'S NAME IS?
Englishman: HMM...
Officer:
WHAT'S THE MATTER, LIMEY?
YOU WANT TO SEE WHAT
A NEW YORK POKEY IS LIKE? HUH?
HERE'S A PRESENT FOR YOU.
( officers laugh )
( Smokey gasps )
Englishman: THAT'S CURIOUS.
HELP ME UNDERSTAND. WHY WOULD
YOU DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
IT'S JUST
SUCH AN UNSAVORY THING TO DO.
Officer: THERE IS NO REASON!
I DO WHAT I LIKE WHENEVER
I FEEL LIKE IT, YOU FOOL!
BUT IF SOMEONE WIPES
A BOOGER ON YOUR FACE,
IT PROBABLY MEANS THAT‐‐
Englishman: YOU'VE MADE
THE WRONG MOVE, YOU STUPID PIG!
( Smokey gasps )
( officer groaning )
Officer #2: YOU WERE SHOT
RESISTING ARREST!
( Englishman spits )
PLEASE, TRY TO SHOOT ME,
BUT I AM WARNING YOU RIGHT NOW,
BEFORE YOU CAN PULL THE TRIGGER,
I WILL HAVE BROKEN YOUR FINGER
LIKE A ROTTEN MATCHSTICK.
Officer #2: NOT FROM OVER THERE!
I'LL BLOW YOUR DAMN BRAINS OUT!
Smokey: SUDDENLY HIS BODY
STARTED TO GIVE OFF
SOME SORT OF GLOW.
IT WAS JUST INCREDIBLE.
THE SODA CAP BLEW OFF AND
FLEW AS FAST AS A BULLET
STRAIGHT OVER
TO SNAP THE COP'S FINGER.
( officer #2 screams )
♪
( officers jabbering )
( Englishman gasps )
I GAVE IN TO MY TEMPER AGAIN.
CRAP. I'M IN FOR IT.
OH, GRANNY ERINA'S
GOING TO BE FURIOUS.
Smokey: HE BEAT DOWN TWO COPS,
BUT IS SCARED OF HIS GRANDMA?
Englishman: I'LL JUST EXPLAIN.
GRANNY ERINA WILL UNDERSTAND
IF I EXPLAIN, WON'T SHE?
ALL RIGHT. MR. PICKPOCKET,
WHAT SAY WE HIGH‐TAIL IT
ON OUT OF HERE?
♪
Smokey: HE DIDN'T KNOW EXACTLY
HOW HE HAD LAUNCHED
THE BOTTLE CAP WITH SUCH FORCE.
HE SAID HE COULD ALWAYS
DO THINGS LIKE THAT.
APPARENTLY HIS GRANDPA COULD
DO THE SAME KIND OF THINGS,
BUT HE DIED AT A YOUNG AGE.
HIS DAD, WHO DIED IN THE WAR,
DIDN'T HAVE
ANY TALENTS LIKE THAT.
HIS MOM WAS GONE, TOO.
I REALLY OWE YOU BIG TIME.
EVERYONE CALLS ME SMOKEY,
AND I'D SURE LIKE IT
IF YOU'D TELL ME YOUR NAME.
JoJo: IT'S JOESTAR,
JOSEPH JOESTAR.
♪
MY FRIENDS CALL ME JOJO.
Straizo: WHAT IS THIS?
WHO IS THAT A CARVING OF
ON THAT PILLAR?
Speedwagon:
THAT'S NOT A CARVING.
HE HAS AMINO ACIDS,
PROTEINS, AND CELLS,
AND THOUGH IT'S FAINT,
HE HAS BODY HEAT AND A PULSE.
WE ARE LOOKING AT A LIVING MAN!
( Straizo grunts )
Speedwagon: STRAIZO, UNDERSTAND,
WHO HE IS,
HOW LONG HE HAS BEEN THERE,
HOW HE GOT THERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
WHAT THE MASKS ARE FOR,
NONE OF THAT MATTERS.
WE ARE HERE
FOR ONE PURPOSE ONLY.
I BROUGHT YOU
BECAUSE OF YOUR HAMON ABILITY,
SO YOU CAN USE IT
TO UTTERLY DESTROY HIM
WHILE HE SLUMBERS IN THIS STONE.
Straizo: AND JOSEPH JOESTAR?
Speedwagon: WHAT?
Straizo: JOSEPH JOESTAR,
HOW IS HE DOING?
I HEAR HE HAS HAMON ABILITY
AND SAVED YOUR LIFE ONCE.
Speedwagon:
WH‐WHY BRING UP JOJO NOW?
Straizo: AS I RECALL, HE WAS
BUT 13 YEARS OF AGE AT THE TIME.
YES, QUITE YOUNG.
YOUR PLANE WAS
HIJACKED BY CRIMINALS
WHO WANTED
TO HOLD YOU FOR RANSOM.
( Speedwagon shuddering )
Hijacker: HEY, KID, YOU CAN'T
STAY BACK HERE, YOU KNOW.
GET UP FRONT!
( JoJo sighs )
YOU'RE HIJACKING THE PLANE
AND KIDNAPPING SPEEDWAGON,
CORRECT?
I AM ONLY A BYSTANDER.
THIS IS HIS PROBLEM.
I'M JUST GOING TO READ MY STORY.
DO YOUR BUSINESS,
AND JUST LEAVE ME OUT OF IT.
( Speedwagon gasps )
Hijacker: WRONG ANSWER, PUNK!
‐ NOW MOVE!
‐ Speedwagon: JOJO.
( JoJo gasps )
( growls )
Speedwagon: NOT GOOD.
THAT SUIT WAS A GIFT FROM ERINA.
THIS'LL SET HIM OFF FOR SURE.
HE'S GOT NO SENSE
OF SELF‐RESTRAINT.
( JoJo growls )
Speedwagon:
CONTROL YOURSELF, JOJO!
JoJo: YOU FELLOWS DID KNOW
THERE WAS
THE POSSIBILITY OF A CRASH
IF YOU HIJACKED THIS PLANE,
DID YOU NOT?
( pilot gasps )
( Speedwagon gasps )
IS THAT HAMON? OH, NO.
♪
( hijackers scream )
Hijacker: WHAT DID
THAT CRAZY KID DO?!
WE'RE GONNA CRASH!
Hijacker #2: GRAB THE CONTROLS!
Hijacker #3:
I CAN'T FLY, IDIOT.
JoJo: HERE. GET THE PILOT READY.
WE'RE GOING TO JUMP.
( explosion )
( both groan )
Speedwagon: WHY CAN'T YOU EVER
JUST THINK THINGS THROUGH, JOJO?
JoJo: I DO IN FACT,
A GREAT DEAL,
MOSTLY ABOUT HOW TO BEST KEEP
YOU AND GRANNY ERINA SAFE.
YOU TWO ARE
THE ONLY FAMILY THAT I'VE GOT.
Speedwagon: HE MAY HAVE
HIS GRANDFATHER'S FACE,
BUT HE'S FAR
FROM BEING A GENTLEMAN.
THAT WAS THE DAY I DISCOVERED
THAT JOSEPH
WAS ABLE TO USE HAMON.
Straizo:
SO YOUNG JOSEPH INHERITED
THE ABILITY TO CONTROL HAMON
FROM HIS GRANDFATHER JONATHAN?
Speedwagon: YES, BUT WHY
ARE YOU SPEAKING OF HIM NOW?
( whoosh )
Speedwagon: WHAT THE HELL?!
Straizo: I JUST TOOK
THE LIVES OF ALL THESE MEN,
AND WHEN YOU LOSE YOUR LIFE,
JONATHAN'S GRANDSON WILL KNOW
GRIEF AND ANGER AND HATE.
HE WILL DEVELOP
A TREMENDOUS HATRED FOR ME.
Speedwagon: NO! STRAIZO!
♪
( squelching )
( footsteps )
Speedwagon: STRAIZO...
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR SENSES?
Straizo: I HAVEN'T.
IN FACT, MY THINKING
IS EXTREMELY CLEAR.
I CHOSE HAMON TO FORGE MY BODY
INTO SOMETHING PURE AND STRONG,
BUT AS I TRAINED,
THE AGING OF MY FLESH
BECAME PAINFULLY CLEAR TO ME.
HAMON PROVIDES ONLY A SMALL
ADVANTAGE OVER ORDINARY PEOPLE.
IT CANNOT GUARD
AGAINST THE PROCESS OF AGING.
IN THE BATTLE WE FOUGHT
SO MANY YEARS AGO,
I SECRETLY ADMIRED DIO.
HE WAS POWERFUL.
HE WAS BEAUTIFUL.
HE WAS IMMORTAL.
I COVETED THE POWER
GRANTED BY THE STONE MASK.
I DIDN'T CARE
WHO GOT IN THE WAY.
( Speedwagon gasps )
YOU'RE A TWISTED TRAITOR,
STRAIZO.
Straizo: YOUR BLOOD
WILL NOW BRING ME IMMORTALITY.
WITH YOU GONE, THE ONLY ONES
TO KNOW OF THE MASK
WILL BE ERINA
AND JOSEPH JOESTAR,
AND ONCE I HAVE
DISPOSED OF THEM,
I SHALL LEARN MORE OF THE MASK
THAN DIO EVER COULD.
Speedwagon: NO, DON'T DO IT.
THE KNOWLEDGE YOU'RE SEEKING
COULD HAVE
TERRIBLE CONSEQUENCES.
( Straizo gags )
( screams )
Speedwagon: JO...JO.
ERINA...
( Straizo gurgling )
( tires squeal )
Driver: HEY, YOU!
WHY DON'T YA GET A CLUE
WHAT YOU'RE DOIN', DUMB‐ASS?
PULL YOUR HEAD OUT OF YOUR BUTT,
AND SEE WHERE YOU ARE!
NOW GET THE HELL OUT OF MY WAY!
( grunts )
JoJo: HELLO THERE.
WHAT? DIDN'T HEAR THAT.
I CAN'T MAKE IT OUT.
WOULD YOU MIND
REPEATING ALL THAT?
I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHAT IT WAS
YOU MEANT TO SAY,
IN CASE I HAVE TO POUND YOU.
‐ ( driver gasps )
‐ Erina: JOJO.
( JoJo gasps )
Erina: WHAT IS IT
YOU'RE DOING THERE?
JoJo: UH, GRANNY ERINA.
Erina: I ASKED WHAT
YOU'RE DOING WITH THAT MAN.
JoJo: UH, WELL, YOU SEE...
THIS MAN IS...
( gasps )
A TAXI!
THIS WAY,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WALK SO FAR.
Erina: THANK YOU, JOJO.
YOU'RE SUCH A THOUGHTFUL BOY.
CLIMB IN, SMOKEY.
WE'RE GOING FOR A RIDE.
♪
Smokey: THE JOESTAR FAMILY,
REDUCED TO A GRANDMOTHER
AND HER GRANDSON.
OVER TIME, I WOULD HEAR
BITS OF THEIR PAST.
JoJo: GRANNY, REALLY.
SPEEDWAGON SENT FOR US,
AND WE CAME
ALL THE WAY TO NEW YORK
SIMPLY BECAUSE HE ASKED,
BUT NOW WE FIND
HE'S NOT EVEN HERE?
I THINK HIS BEHAVIOR
IS QUITE RUDE.
Erina: I'M SURE
THAT THE OIL BUSINESS
REQUIRES MUCH OF HIS TIME.
( JoJo groans )
HMM.
SAY, GRANNY...
Erina: HMM?
JoJo: I'M CURIOUS.
WAS SPEEDWAGON
REALLY GRANDPA'S BEST FRIEND?
IS THAT ALL IT WAS?
COME ON NOW.
Erina: WHAT ARE YOU IMPLYING?
Speedwagon: WELL, LET'S SEE.
HE WAS NEVER MARRIED, WAS HE?
AND YOU YOURSELF ARE A WIDOW.
WELL, IT LEADS ME TO WONDER
IF SIMPLE FRIENDSHIP
WAS THE ONLY RELATIONSHIP
THAT WAS GOING ON THERE.
( Erina scoffs )
YOU ROGUE, YOU!
‐ JoJo: SORRY. OW! I WAS WRONG.
‐ ( thumping )
OW! FORGIVE ME. AAH!
I KNOW SPEEDWAGON IS LOYAL. OW!
AGH! OW!
Smokey: THE JOESTARS
TENDED TO BE SHORT‐LIVED.
GRANNY ERINA LOST HER HUSBAND
IN AN ACCIDENT AT SEA.
SHE WAS PREGNANT
WITH A SON AT THE TIME.
WHEN HE GREW UP,
HE MARRIED A GIRL
WHO HAD ALSO SURVIVED THE WRECK.
THEY WERE JOJO'S PARENTS,
LATER CLAIMED
BY WAR AND DISEASE.
GRANNY ERINA WAS
A GENTLE AND GIVING WOMAN,
EVEN TO PUNKS LIKE ME
OR ANYBODY ELSE.
MAYBE IT WAS BECAUSE
SHE LIVED WITH LONELINESS.
JOJO WAS THE SAME.
THIS TIME, HOWEVER, HIS BASIC
KINDNESS GOT HIM INTO TROUBLE...
( overlapping chatter )
...THANKS TO ME.
Man: HEY, WAITER. WAITER!
Waiter: YES, SIR?
Man: WHO DECIDED
THAT STINKIN' ANIMAL
COULD BE ALLOWED IN HERE, HUH?
HUH?!
♪
HIS SMELL
IS RUININ' MY APPETITE.
THAT KIND SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
Waiter: I UNDERSTAND, SIR,
BUT THERE IS A POLICY
HANDED DOWN BY MANAGEMENT.
AS LONG AS THE CHECK
IS PAID IN FULL,
WE HAPPILY SERVE ANYONE.
Man: WHAT WAS THAT?
YOU'LL HAPPILY
LET BEASTS LIKE THAT
DO THEIR GRAZING IN HERE? HUH?
Smokey: UH, GUESS I'LL
JUST BE ON MY WAY.
( JoJo growls )
Erina: JOJO.
JoJo: YOU HEARD HIM. COME ON.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TELL ME
TO STOP, ARE YOU?
Erina: NO. PEOPLE ARE
ENTITLED TO THEIR OPINIONS.
BUT THIS MISBEGOTTEN OAF
HAS GIVEN PUBLIC INSULT
TO OUR FRIEND.
BE MINDFUL
OF THE OTHER GUESTS NOW,
BUT TEACH HIM A LESSON.
Man #2: HMM.
JoJo: I WAS HOPING
YOU'D SAY THAT.
( man #1 laughs )
WELL, NOW, BOY,
LOOKIN' TO FIGHT?
( knuckles crack )
JoJo: LET ME HELP.
IF THE BRASS KNUCKLES
ARE WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR,
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO FIND THEM
INSIDE OF YOUR COAT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO CHECK
YOUR BACK POCKET INSTEAD.
Man #1: WHA?
‐ ( diners murmur)
‐ Smokey: WHAT?
Man #1: EH? NO WAY.
EH?
JoJo: NEXT YOU'LL SAY,
"YOU BASTARD,
HOW COULD YOU HAVE POSSIBLY
KNOWN WHERE THEY WERE?"
Man #1: YOU BASTARD,
HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY HAVE KNOWN
WHERE THEY WERE?
HUH?!
JoJo: BY THE VISIBLE ABRASIONS
THAT ARE ON YOUR RIGHT HAND,
IT'S OBVIOUS
THAT YOU DO YOUR FIGHTING
USING BRASS KNUCKLES.
YOU'VE NO WOUNDS,
SO THE THE BLOOD ON YOUR SHIRT
IS NOT FROM YOU.
‐ ( man #1 yells )
‐ JoJo: THEREFORE,
YOU'VE JUST COME FROM A FIGHT.
SINCE THE BLOOD
IS ON YOUR SHIRT
AND NOT THAT PINK HORROR
OF A COAT,
IT WAS TAKEN OFF
PRIOR TO THE FIGHT.
AND THEN AFTER YOU
HAD COMPLETED YOUR ASSAULT,
THE KNUCKLES CAME OFF,
AND THAT'S WHEN YOU PROCEEDED
TO STOW THEM AWAY
IN YOUR BACK POCKET.
( man #1 growls )
JoJo: FOR MY NEXT GLIMPSE
INTO THE FUTURE,
YOU WILL NOW SAY,
"SO WHAT, YOU LITTLE PUNK?"
Man #1: YEAH, SO WHAT,
YOU LITTLE PUNK?
AND NOW YOU'RE GONNA GET IT.
I GOT YA!
( grunting )
YOU LIKE THAT, HUH?
THAT'LL TEACH YOU A LESSON.
JoJo: SORRY. YOU MISSED.
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN PUNCHING?
I WASN'T THE ONE
YOU WERE PUMMELING SO HAPPILY.
Man #1: OH, MY GOD!
( groans )
JoJo: I CAN PREDICT AND COUNTER
ANYTHING YOUR TINY BRAIN
IS ABLE TO COME UP WITH.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT NOW,
YOU SIMPLETON?
( crowd laughs )
Man #2: PLEASE,
FORGIVE THE BEHAVIOR
OF MY UNDERLING, MADAM.
YOU'RE ERINA JOESTAR,
AREN'T YOU?
I'VE WORKED ON A LOT
OF BUSINESS DEALS
WITH YOUR MR. SPEEDWAGON,
YOU SEE.
HE TOLD ME SOME STORIES
ABOUT YOU
WHEN HIM AND ME WERE IN LONDON
A WHILE BACK.
I'M GLAD TO MEET YOU.
I HEARD A LITTLE SOMETHING
THROUGH THE GRAPEVINE.
IT HASN'T MADE IT
INTO THE PAPERS YET,
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW.
IT SEEMS THAT MR. SPEEDWAGON
HAS BEEN MURDERED.
( both gasp )
JoJo: ARE YOU SURE?
Man #2: RUMOR IS
THE CAT WHO DID IT
WAS SOME SORT
OF TIBETAN MONK.
JoJo: SOME SORT OF MONK?
COULD IT BE STRAIZO?
Man #2: ALL THEY'RE SAYING IS
THAT THE BODIES OF SPEEDWAGON
AND HIS TEAM WASHED UP
ALONG A RIVERBANK
SOMEWHERE DOWN IN MEXICO.
IT'S A GENUINE MYSTERY.
NOBODY HAS ANY IDEA
WHY THEY WERE KILLED
OR WHERE THE MONK
MIGHT HAVE GONE TO AFTERWARD.
( JoJo and Erina gasp )
Erina: ACTUALLY,
I THINK I MIGHT KNOW.
PERHAPS.
SPEEDWAGON SAID SOMETHING
A LONG TIME AGO.
IT INVOLVED DIO
AND THE HORRIBLE STONE MASK
THAT CHANGED HIM.
Smokey: JOJO,
THAT GUY IS A MAFIA MAN.
YOU CAN'T TRUST
WHAT HE TELLS YOU.
HE'S TRYING TO PULL SOMETHING!
Man #2: BELIEVE WHATEVER
YOU WANT TO, KID.
JoJo: HOLD ON.
TRY YOUR BREAST POCKET
‐ IF YOU'RE AFTER YOUR LIGHTER.
‐ Man #2: EH?
JoJo: ANYWAY,
THANKS FOR THE WARNING, SMOKEY.
BUT I THINK I BELIEVE
WHAT THIS MAN IS TELLING US.
THESE FELLOWS ARE ONLY
MOTIVATED BY MONEY.
CLEARLY INFORMATION LIKE THAT
IS VALUABLE TO HIS ORGANIZATION,
SO I'M INCLINED
TO LISTEN TO HIM.
HOWEVER...
( man #2 groaning )
JoJo: AS TRUE AS THAT MAY BE,
YOU DON'T SIMPLY WALTZ OVER HERE
AND THEN JUST BLURT OUT
AWFUL NEWS TO GRANNY ERINA.
DON'T YOU SEE HOW BADLY UPSET
YOU'VE MADE HER WITH THIS NEWS?
YOU ARE VERY THOUGHTLESS!
( man #2 yelps )
Erina: IT WAS 50 YEARS AGO,
AND STILL THOSE EVENTS HAUNT US.
JoJo: DON'T BE FRIGHTENED.
I'M HERE,
AND I'LL PROTECT YOU.
Erina: YOU MUSTN'T, JOSEPH.
I'M CONCERNED FOR YOU.
I DON'T WANT YOU SNARED BY EVIL
FROM A HALF‐CENTURY AGO.
JoJo: I'LL BE FINE, GRANNY.
IF THIS IS MY FATE,
I ACCEPT IT FULLY.
♪
Smokey: AT THE TIME,
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT WAS GOING ON,
BUT THESE TWO
HAD AN UNIMAGINABLE HISTORY.
JoJo: HEY, SMOKEY.
Smokey: HMM?
WHAT'S GOING ON, JOJO?
JoJo: LOOK AT THIS HERE.
SEE WHAT THEY'RE SAYING?
Smokey: WHAT IS IT?
JoJo: DO YOU THINK THIS IS TRUE?
CAN GIRLS REALLY
MAKE THEM BIGGER? WHOO‐HOO.
Smokey: LET'S SEE.
"GO FROM AN AA CUP TO A C CUP."
HAH! RIGHT.
JUST A BUNCH OF SNAKE OIL.
DON'T BUY INTO IT.
JoJo: COME AGAIN?
Smokey: I THINK $1.25
A PAIR IS TOO MUCH.
♪
JoJo: HMM.
UH, NO.
YES, BUT...
I SAY...
YOU LOOK RATHER FAMILIAR TO ME,
YET SOMEHOW DIFFERENT.
PLEASE TELL ME, HAVE WE
POSSIBLY MET SOMEWHERE BEFORE?
AND WHY ISN'T
YOUR BREATH VISIBLE?
IT'S SO COLD TONIGHT.
AND IF MY EYES
AREN'T DECEIVING ME,
I THINK I CAUGHT A GLIMPSE
OF FANGS IN YOUR MOUTH JUST NOW.
WAS I SEEING THINGS?
DON'T TRIFLE WITH ME.
I WARN YOU.
Straizo: HEH.
EVEN IF IT IS IN PLAIN SIGHT
ON THIS CITY STREET, JOJO,
I'LL TAKE YOUR LIFE LONG BEFORE
YOU EVER BECOME A DANGER.
JoJo: OR PERHAPS NOT.
( Straizo gasps )
( woman screams )
Smokey: I KNEW
THE MAN WAS CRAZY,
BUT NOT THAT CRAZY!
RIGHT OUT IN PUBLIC?
INCREDIBLE!
WHERE DID HE EVEN
GET THE TOMMY GUN?!
WHY SHOOT UP THE WHOLE CITY?!
( JoJo yells )
( bystanders yell )
( glass tinkling )
♪
JoJo: YES,
I WAS AWAITING YOU, STRAIZO.
THAT WAS ON BEHALF
OF SPEEDWAGON,
BUT I DON'T THINK
YOU'LL GO DOWN SO EASILY.
OUR WAR HAS BEGUN.
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
JoJo: STRAIZO IS
INDEED A VAMPIRE.
‐ NOW YOU'RE MINE!
‐ Nazi: GERMAN MEDICINE
IS THE GREATEST THING
IN THE WORLD, DON'T YOU THINK?
Speedwagon: YOU DON'T KNOW
THE FORCES YOU'RE PLAYING WITH!
JoJo: GIVE MY BEST
TO SPEEDWAGON IN HELL!