( wind blowing )
JoJo: ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH.
SOMETHING'S GOING ON HERE.
I'VE FELT LIKE SOMEONE'S EYES
HAVE BEEN ON ME ALL MORNING
WATCHING MY EVERY MOVE.
WHY? CLEARLY I'M ALONE.
NOBODY COULD HAVE FOLLOWED ME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE.
I'M OUT
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
BUT I CAN'T SHAKE THE FEELING
THAT SOMEONE'S HERE!
DAMN MY IMAGINATION.
MUST BE THE HEAT
PLAYING TRICKS WITH MY MIND.
♪
( groans )
( man, German accent )
WELL, AREN'T YOU A SHARP ONE?
YOU SOMEHOW SENSED MY PRESENCE
ALTHOUGH I WAS ENGAGING
MY SKILLS OF STEALTH
THIS ENTIRE TIME.
EVEN WILD BATS CAN'T DO THAT.
JoJo: WHY THE HELL
ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME?
I'VE GOT NO BUSINESS WITH YOU.
Man: OH, I'M NOT FOLLOWING.
I'M IN THE BUSINESS
OF CAPTURING, SEE?
OUR ARMY WOULD LIKE
TO ASK YOU SOME QUESTIONS
ABOUT STRAIZO, JOSEPH JOESTAR!
JoJo: STRAIZO? WHY WOULD
YOU BE INTERESTED IN HIM?
AND WHO IS "OUR ARMY"?
♪
( singing in Japanese )
JoJo: BY YOUR ACCENT,
THE CUT OF YOUR FACE,
AND YOUR SMELL,
I'D GUESS YOU'RE GERMAN.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT BUSINESS
A THUG LIKE YOU HAS
WITH EITHER STRAIZO
OR SPEEDWAGON.
BUT IF YOU'RE
NOT GONNA SAY ANYTHING,
I DON'T MIND HAVING TO BEAT
SOME ANSWERS OUT OF YOU.
Donovan: YOU THINK
YOU CAN TAKE ON THE BLADE
OF S. S. COMMANDER DONOVAN
WITH JUST YOUR BARE HANDS,
LITTLE BOY?
( slurps )
I'M ALMOST INSULTED.
BUT SINCE YOU INSIST,
I'M HAPPY TO OBLIGE!
JoJo: GREAT, BUT HOW 'BOUT
I GIVE YOU BACK
YOUR FLEA‐RIDDEN MAGIC RAG?
( screams )
( groans )
CACTUS NEEDLES.
♪
( groans )
Donovan: VICTORY.
I REALLY THOUGHT
THAT YOU WERE GOING TO GIVE ME
MORE OF A CHALLENGE THERE.
WHAT HAPPENED, LITTLE BOY?
REPEAT AFTER ME.
"I NEVER SHOULD HAVE CHALLENGED
YOUR SUPERIOR POWER,
HERR DONOVAN."
JoJo: I‐‐I NEVER
SHOULD HAVE CHALLENGED YOUR...
SUPERIOR POWER.
Donovan: WHAT'S THAT?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
JoJo: I UNDERESTIMATED
YOUR ETIQUETTE.
Donovan: HUH?
JoJo: YOU REALLY ARE
QUITE THE GENTLEMAN
FOR LETTING ME REST RIGHT HERE
AND GIVING ME THESE MOMENTS
TO RECOVER SAFELY.
Donovan: WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
RECOVER SAFELY?
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND,
LITTLE BOY?
WAIT A SEC. WHAT'S THIS?
WHAT'S UP WITH THIS CACTUS?
JoJo: YOU SHOULD
TAKE A CLOSER LOOK.
( Donovan screams )
( gasping )
JoJo: THAT CACTUS WAS MY GOAL
ALL ALONG, HERR DONOVAN.
CACTI ARE MADE UP
OF NEARLY 95% WATER,
AND THEY'RE KNOWN TO BE
FABULOUS CONDUCTORS OF HAMON.
NOW THEN,
REPEAT AFTER ME, HERR DONOVAN.
"I PROMISE TO TELL
JOSEPH JOESTAR EVERYTHING."
♪
OKAY, THEN.
WHEN SPEEDWAGON'S BODY
DISAPPEARED,
I SWORE TO MYSELF
THAT I WOULD NEVER GIVE UP HOPE,
NO MATTER WHAT.
TURNS OUT HE WAS SAFE ALL ALONG.
MAN, IT'S NICE TO HEAR
SOME GOOD NEWS FOR A CHANGE.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO TELL GRANNY ERINA.
SHE'LL BE SO HAPPY
TO HEAR ABOUT THIS.
ALTHOUGH,
THERE'S NO WAY OF TELLING
HOW THE GERMANS HAVE
ACTUALLY BEEN TREATING HIM.
REGARDLESS, I'LL BRING HIM HOME,
AND GRANNY ERINA'S SMILE
WILL SHINE LIKE THE MIDDAY SUN.
Donovan: HEY, DON'T LEAVE!
( blood flowing )
Scientist:
LOOK, MAJOR VON STROHEIM!
THE PILLAR'S SHELL
IS STARTING TO CRACK.
Scientist #2:
IT'S CURRENTLY HOLDING
THE BLOOD OF FIVE PRISONERS.
WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT ITS FULL CAPABILITIES ARE.
FEEDING IT ANY MORE
COULD PUSH IT BEYOND
OUR ESTABLISHED SAFETY ZONE.
Von Stroheim: HMM.
I'M CURIOUS HOW THE BLOOD
WAS EXTRACTED
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
NO, WAIT! I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
I CAN IMAGINE WHAT SORT
OF THINGS YOU CAME UP WITH.
♪
( gargles )
OH, SPEEDWAGON.
NO NEED TO LOOK SO PALE.
I TOLD YOU FROM THE START
THERE WAS NOTHING TO FEAR.
Speedwagon:
STOP BEING SO ARROGANT!
YOU'VE NO IDEA
WHAT HE'S CAPABLE OF!
Von Stroheim: RELAX, OLD MAN.
THAT TEST CHAMBER
IS IMPENETRABLE.
IT HAS IRON WALLS
NEARLY 20 INCHES THICK.
IT'S EQUIPPED WITH
FLAMETHROWERS, MACHINE GUNS,
UND EXPLOSIVES
IF WE NEED THEM.
I SHOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
THAT ALL OF YOUR COURAGE
DOESN'T EVEN ADD UP TO
WHAT I HAVE IN MY LITTLE FINGER.
YOU COWARD!
WANT TO KNOW WHAT I THINK,
SPEEDWAGON?
I THINK THAT THING
IS SIMPLY A STATUE
OF PETRIFIED CAVEMAN BONES
THAT'S WASTING MY TIME!
Soldier: MAJOR! HE'S ERUPTING!
‐ ( Speedwagon gasps )
‐ Von Stroheim: HMM?
Soldier #2: IT'S BLOOD!
THAT BLOOD IT TOOK IN
IS SPRAYING OUT EVERYWHERE!
I CAN'T SEE A THING!
Von Stroheim:
ACTIVATE THE SPRINKLER SYSTEM!
( all gasp )
♪
( Von Stroheim chuckles )
Scientist #1: HIS OUTER LAYER
IS TRANSFORMING.
IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S MORPHING INTO FLESH.
HE'S TRYING TO MOVE.
I‐I THINK HE'S ALIVE!
( Von Stroheim laughs )
WELL, HE'LL NEED A NAME,
SOMETHING BETTER THAN
"THE PILLAR MAN."
AS HIS NEW GODFATHER, I SUPPOSE
THIS TASK FALLS ONTO ME.
LET ME SEE.
I'LL NAME HIM
AFTER THE MEXICAN WINDS.
HE SHALL BE KNOWN AS SANTVIENTO.
LOOK. HE'S TRYING TO STAND.
RISE BEFORE US.
RISE UP, UND SHOW US
WHAT YOU ARE MADE OF...
SANTVIENTO!
( Santviento groans )
‐ ( scientists gasping )
‐ Von Stroheim: HMM?
( Santviento sniffing )
( water splashes )
( joints popping )
( massaging )
( Von Stroheim laughing )
‐ ( laughter continues )
‐ ( Speedwagon gasping )
Von Stroheim: YOU SEE THAT?
SANTVIENTO MIGHT HAVE A FUTURE
DOING COMEDY IN THE CABARET.
THE ULTIMATE ORGANISM?
MORE LIKE THE ULTIMATE IDIOT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK THERE,
SPEEDWAGON?
HE'S GOT THE BRAINS
OF A FERAL ANIMAL.
HE'S TRYING TO SMELL
HIS WAY AROUND.
HE'S REALLY
JUST A PRIMITIVE MAN.
( Speedwagon gasping )
Von Stroheim: THIS IS A FARCE.
REGARDLESS, LET'S JUST MOVE ON
UND ASSUME HE MADE THE MASKS.
YOU THERE,
START THE EXPERIMENT.
SOMEBODY OPEN THE DOOR
TO THE NEXT CHAMBER.
Soldier #3: YES, SIR!
( door grinding )
♪
Speedwagon: WHAT‐‐
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
Von Stroheim: A PRISONER.
WELL, A PRISONER
WITH A MASK, ACTUALLY.
Speedwagon: IS‐‐
IS THAT A VAMPIRE?
Von Stroheim:
ONLY A FEW DAYS AGO,
THAT THING WAS
A FEEBLE, TOOTHLESS OLD MAN
KNOCKING ON DEATH'S DOOR.
WE STILL HAVEN'T FED HIM TODAY,
SO HE MUST BE THIRSTY.
I THINK HE'LL GO
STRAIGHT FOR THE ATTACK.
WHO WILL WIN?
I CAN HARDLY WAIT.
( vampire yells )
Von Stroheim: WHAT? THAT'S ALL?
HE DIDN'T EVEN PUT UP A FIGHT.
HE'S AN ORDINARY MAN AFTER ALL.
Scientist #2: WE DON'T
HAVE ANY OTHER SUBJECTS
FOR THIS TEST,
MAJOR VON STROHEIM.
Scientist #3:
WE PLANTED EXPLOSIVES
IN THE PRISONER'S HEAD
FOR THIS EXACT SITUATION.
JUST GIVE US THE WORD, AND WE'LL
ACTIVATE THEM IMMEDIATELY.
Scientist #2: MAJOR?
Von Stroheim: FINE.
( vampire growls )
( Santviento grunts )
( flowing )
( Speedwagon gasps )
Von Stroheim: WAIT! STOP!
I RESCIND THE ORDER!
HIS JAW, LOOK.
WHAT'S HAPPENING THERE
WITH HIS JAW?
HIS HANDS, HIS ARMS.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HIS ARMS?
I'D GIVEN HIM UP FOR DEAD
IN THE BEGINNING,
BUT LOOK. SANTVIENTO IS
SOMEHOW ABSORBING THE PRISONER.
( vampire screaming )
‐ ( crunching )
‐ ( screaming continues )
Von Stroheim: HE'S PULLING HIM
STRAIGHT INTO HIS BODY.
HE'S DEVOURING HIM!
WHAT A MARVELOUS CREATURE.
THE MASKED MAN WAS NO MORE
THAN FODDER FOR HIM.
SANTVIENTO FEEDS
WITH HIS ENTIRE BODY,
SO‐‐SO NOTHING IS LOST.
HE CAN ABSORB EVERY BIT
OF HIS PREY'S LIFE FORCE
DOWN TO THE LAST DROP.
( Speedwagon gasping )
Soldier #1: HE ATE HIM!
HE ACTUALLY ATE THE MASKED MAN.
Soldier #3: HOW IS THAT
EVEN POSSIBLE?!
Soldier #4: UND NOW LOOK!
HE'S‐‐HE'S GROWN SOMETHING.
Von Stroheim: GET A GRIP.
AS LONG AS HE'S
STILL IN THAT CHAMBER,
HE CAN'T HURT YOU.
HE JUST GAINED A LITTLE WEIGHT
AFTER HIS FEEDING.
THAT'S ALL IT IS.
Speedwagon:
HIS‐‐HIS INTELLIGENCE?
AND WHAT ABOUT
HIS INTELLIGENCE?
WHAT LEVEL OF THOUGHT
IS HE CAPABLE OF?
Von Stroheim: HUH?
Santviento:
MA‐MAJOR VON STRO‐STROHEIM.
Von Stroheim: WHAT?!
BUT HOW DID HE‐‐
HE SAID‐‐
HOW DID HE KNOW MY NAME?
HE'S NOT EVEN
SUPPOSED TO BE ABLE
TO HEAR ANYTHING FROM IN THERE!
♪
JoJo: THERE IT IS.
ACCORDING TO MY DANGLING
CACTUS PAL DONOVAN,
THE UNDERGROUND FACILITY
I'M LOOKING FOR
IS HIDDEN DOWN THERE SOMEWHERE.
IF HE WAS TELLING THE TRUTH,
SPEEDWAGON SHOULD BE INSIDE.
SO NOW HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO GET IN THERE?
Soldier: VEGETABLES,
CANNED GOODS,
MEAT, HAM, EGGS.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT A NICE
BASKET OF FOOD THERE, ALL RIGHT.
( women whimpering )
Soldier #2: NOW THEN,
IT'S TIME FOR THE FRISKING.
Soldier #1: AW, COME ON NOW.
STOP MAKING THAT FACE.
YOU CAN GIVE ME A LITTLE SMILE.
Soldier #2: LIFT UP YOUR SKIRTS,
AND SMILE.
HMM.
( chuckles )
( women shudder )
Soldier #2:
YOU'RE CLEARED TO GO. NEXT!
( JoJo, high voice )
ALL I'VE GOT UNDER MY SKIRT
IS MORE TEQUILA, BIG BOY.
IS IT ALL RIGHT
TO BRING THAT THROUGH, TOO?
‐ Soldier #2: HMM?
‐ Soldier #1: EH?
( JoJo moans )
Soldier #1:
HANDS UP IN THE AIR!
Soldier #2: ANY FUNNY MOVES,
AND WE SHOOT YOU DEAD!
JoJo: WHAT? PUT YOUR GUNS DOWN.
I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
Soldier #2:
THAT'S A FUNNY MOVE THERE.
Soldier #1: FIRE.
JoJo: NO! PLEASE DON'T SHOOT!
I'M NOT MOVING, AND I'VE
GOT MY HANDS IN THE AIR!
( normal )
ALL RIGHT. DAMN.
YOU GERMANS ARE SO SMART.
YOU SAW THROUGH MY DISGUISE
ALMOST IMMEDIATELY.
Soldier #1: ARE YOU CRAZY?
OF COURSE WE SAW
THROUGH THAT THING.
YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
Soldier #2: EVEN MY BIG SISTER
ISN'T AS UGLY AS YOU,
AND WE USED HER TO PLOW
THE FIELDS. SHE WAS AN OX.
YOU SHOULD'VE SPENT MORE TIME
IN FRONT OF THE MIRROR
THIS MORNING, BIG SISSY!
JoJo: WHAT WAS THAT?
( soldiers chuckle )
JoJo: HAMON!
Soldiers: OH, JEEZ.
( bodies thump )
JoJo: WELL, THAT WAS
DISAPPOINTINGLY EASY.
IF I CAN GET THIS THING TO FIT,
THIS UNIFORM
SHOULD WORK NICELY.
Scientist #1: WHAT‐‐
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Scientist #2: I‐‐I DON'T KNOW.
Soldier #3: YOU DON'T KNOW?
WEREN'T YOU WATCHING?
Scientist #3:
MAJOR VON STROHEIM,
I ONLY LOOKED AWAY FOR A MOMENT.
SURELY YOU UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, YOU WERE HERE
AS WELL, RIGHT?
EVERYBODY HERE WAS WATCHING.
IT JUST HAPPENS
THAT NOBODY SAW ANYTHING.
Von Stroheim:
PUT THAT COFFEE DOWN!
Scientist #3: IT‐‐IT WAS
ONLY FOR A MOMENT.
I TOOK MY EYES OFF HIM
FOR JUST A FEW SECONDS.
THAT'S ALL. I SWEAR.
IT MAKES NO SENSE.
I MEAN, MY VISION IS PERFECT,
WE ALL HAVE A CLEAR VIEW,
BUT WE DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED!
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE!
( Speedwagon gasping )
Scientist #3: THE CHAMBER
IS COMPLETELY SEALED,
UND STILL THE SUBJECT
MANAGED TO ESCAPE!
Scientist #2: NONE OF THE WALLS
SHOW ANY SIGN OF DAMAGE.
Von Stroheim:
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU SAW.
I WANT HIM FOUND.
SOMEWHERE INSIDE THE CHAMBER.
SIMPLY CUT OFF
THE OXYGEN SUPPLY IN THERE.
HE'LL TURN UP WHEN HE
FINDS OUT HE CAN'T BREATHE.
Soldier #5:
THE RECORDED FILM IS NOW READY
FOR YOUR VIEWING,
MAJOR VON STROHEIM.
Von Stroheim:
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
‐ SET IT UP.
‐ Soldier #5: YES, SIR.
♪
Von Stroheim: ROLL THE FILM.
SEE THAT?
HE'S RUNNING TOWARDS THE WALL.
JA, BUT WHY?
( joints popping )
( all gasp )
Von Stroheim: WAS IST LOS?
HE'S SQUEEZING HIMSELF
INTO THE VENTILATION DUCTS!
THOSE SLATS ARE LESS
THAN TWO INCHES TALL.
HOW THE HELL COULD ANYONE
POSSIBLY STUFF AN ENTIRE BODY
THROUGH A GAP THAT SMALL?!
Speedwagon: INCREDIBLE.
HE DIDN'T
SIMPLY DISLOCATE HIS JOINTS.
HE SOMEHOW DISASSEMBLED
HIS ENTIRE SKELETON
SO THAT HE COULD COMPLETELY
ALTER HIS SHAPE AT WILL.
( Germans gasping )
( Speedwagon gasps )
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS.
HE IS NOW
WANDERING AROUND FREELY
SOMEWHERE IN YOUR BASE'S
VENTILATION SYSTEM.
Scientist #2: SANTVIENTO ALREADY
KNEW YOUR NAME SOMEHOW,
MAJOR VON STROHEIM,
AND I THINK I MIGHT KNOW HOW.
THE ONLY WAY
THAT WOULD BE POSSIBLE
IS IF HE HEARD YOUR NAME
THROUGH THE VENTS.
Von Stroheim: THE VENTS
LEAD DIRECTLY INTO THIS ROOM?
YOU, SOLDIER, TURN AROUND,
AND MOVE AWAY
FROM THAT VENT IMMEDIATELY.
GO, YOU IDIOT!
Soldier #6: UH...
( sighs )
( screams )
( soldier #6 screams )
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
MAJOR VON STROHEIM!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
WHERE DID EVERYBODY GO?!
AND WHY IS IT SO DARK IN HERE?!
WHY CAN'T I SEE ANYTHING?!
SOMEBODY, PLEASE HELP ME!
I CAN'T SEE!
WHAT'S HE DOING TO ME?!
Speedwagon: SANTVIENTO IS
TRYING TO TAKE CONTROL
OF THAT SOLDIER'S BODY.
‐ ( Germans gasping )
‐ Soldier #6: SOMEONE, ANYONE,
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME ALONE!
YOU CAN'T ABANDON ME.
DON'T LEAVE ME HERE
WITH HIM INSIDE‐‐
( grunting )
WELL, WELL,
I DON'T FULLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE,
BUT I FEEL LIKE I'M PRACTICALLY
BURSTING WITH NEW LIFE.
Von Stroheim:
WHAT A CATASTROPHE.
IF THIS THING ESCAPES,
I'LL BE KNOWN
FOR CREATING THE FATHERLAND'S
MOST POWERFUL ENEMY.
Scientist #2:
WE MUST DESTROY HIM.
Von Stroheim: AT THIS POINT,
IT'S EITHER HIM OR US.
VERY WELL! TAKE HIM OUT!
OPEN FIRE, AND SHRED
THAT MONSTER TO PIECES!
Soldier #6: OOH. HEH.
STOP. THAT TICKLES.
( laughs )
( grunting )
( soldier #3 yelps )
HE'S STILL ALIVE!
Soldier #4: IMPOSSIBLE!
Soldier #7: THE BULLETS,
THEY HAVE NO EFFECT ON HIM.
( Von Stroheim gasping )
Soldier #8: HE'S AN ABOMINATION.
( soldiers shuddering )
Soldier #7: WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
Soldier #8: WHY IS HE
POINTING AT US?
Von Stroheim: NOBODY MOVE.
DON'T YOU SEE HE'S IMITATING
ONE OF YOUR MACHINE GUNS?
LOOK. HE'S JUST COPYING
WHAT HE'S SEEING.
SO WHEN HE SPOKE EARLIER,
HE ONLY SAID MY NAME,
BUT DID NOT UNDERSTAND IT,
WHICH MEANS
HE'S NOT INTELLIGENT.
HE JUST APES WHAT HE SEES,
UND THAT GIVES ME A GREAT IDEA.
IF HE'S ONLY CAPABLE
OF ACTING LIKE A MONKEY,
WE SHOULD START PREPARATIONS
FOR USING HIM LIKE ONE.
Santviento: YOU...
WHICH ONE OF YOU...
WAS FOOL ENOUGH
TO DISTURB MY SLUMBER?
Von Stroheim: HE‐‐HE SPOKE.
Speedwagon: HE'S CLEARLY
CAPABLE OF HIGHER THOUGHT.
I'D BET HE POSSESSES
A GREAT INTELLIGENCE.
HE JUST LEARNED OUR LANGUAGE.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND THAT HE
DID THAT IN ALMOST NO TIME?
( Von Stroheim shudders )
‐ Santviento: DIE.
‐ ( Von Stroheim gasps )
‐ ( soldiers gasping )
‐ Soldier #7: WHAT THE...
( soldier #8 screaming )
Soldier #3: THAT MUST HAVE
BEEN ONE OF OUR BULLETS.
HE'S SHOOTING AT US.
HE'S GONNA KILL US ALL!
Soldier #9: LET'S GO, OLD MAN.
WE BETTER GET YOU TO SAFETY.
THERE'S NO TELLING
HOW MANY MORE BULLETS
THAT MONSTER
MIGHT HAVE INSIDE OF HIM.
Speedwagon: JUST LEAVE ME.
THE LAST THING I NEED RIGHT NOW
IS HELP
FROM A GERMAN FLUNKY.
Soldier #9: WHAT A PAIN.
YOU NEVER CHANGE.
I'M GLAD TO SEE THAT YOU'RE
STILL JUST AS STUBBORN AS EVER.
( Speedwagon gasps )
( Germans gasping )
♪
( Von Stroheim shrieks )
S‐SOMEBODY DO SOMETHING!
OPEN FIRE!
NO! STAY AWAY!
Soldier #9: PARDON ME.
I'LL NEED A BIT OF YOUR HAIR.
JUST A SMALL HANDFUL OR TWO.
Von Stroheim: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?! LET ME GO!
Soldier #9: THE MORE YOU FIGHT,
THE MORE IT'LL HURT.
Von Stroheim: YOU'RE ASSAULTING
A SUPERIOR OFFICER! OW!
Speedwagon: WHO ARE YOU?
I KNOW THAT DEMEANOR,
BUT IT COULDN'T BE.
♪
JoJo: I CALL THIS ONE,
THE OLD HAMON HAIR ATTACK!
♪
( Speedwagon gasps )
BUT THAT MEANS‐‐
THAT MEANS YOU'RE...
JOSEPH JOESTAR!
( bullets firing )
JoJo: BARRIER UP!
( sizzling )
♪
YOU'RE GONNA LOSE YOUR HAIR
IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL,
MR. GERMAN ARMY MAN.
THAT FELT LIKE SANDPAPER.
YOU SHOULD CONSIDER INVESTING
IN A DECENT MOISTURIZER.
Speedwagon: BUT HOW LONG
HAVE YOU BEEN HERE, JOSEPH?
JoJo: EH, JUST GOT HERE.
Santviento: H‐HAIR.
JoJo: SORRY I TOOK SO LONG.
I'D HAVE BEEN HERE SOONER
IF I'D KNOWN WHAT KIND
OF PARTY WAS GOING ON.
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Speedwagon: HE'S USING
HIS ADVANCED INTELLECT
TO LEARN EVERYTHING.
JoJo: WORK WITH ME HERE.
MAKE SOME LOVE TO THE CAMERA.
Santviento: YOU LOWLY PRIMITIVE.