( vampires cheering )
Narrator: BATTLE
FOR THE RED STONE OF AJA,
JOJO VERSUS WAMUU
IN A ONE‐ON‐ONE CHARIOT DUEL.
( vampire horses roar )
Kars: THE TIME IS UPON US.
WHEN THE FULL MOON ONCE AGAIN
EMERGES FROM BEHIND THAT CLOUD,
THE BATTLE WILL BEGIN!
( vampires cheer )
WAMUU! WAMUU! WAMUU...
JoJo: I WISH THEY
WOULDN'T MAKE ALL THAT NOISE.
WHY IS IT THAT THE BAD GUYS
GET ALL THE FANS?
Wamuu: ONE LAP IS 960 METERS.
IT TAKES
APPROXIMATELY ONE MINUTE
FOR THESE BEASTS
TO COMPLETE A LAP.
DO YOU SEE
THAT COLUMN OVER THERE?
ON EACH LAP, A DIFFERENT WEAPON
WILL BE HANGING FROM IT.
JoJo: WEAPONS?
Wamuu: NO.
ONE WEAPON AT A TIME.
WHICHEVER OF US CAN CAPTURE
THAT COLUMN BEFORE THE OTHER
WILL THEN HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY
TO WIELD THE WEAPON.
DO YOU SEE
THE FIRST ONE UP THERE?
IT'S A GIANT SLEDGEHAMMER.
( vampires cheer )
( JoJo gasps )
THAT THING COULD SMASH RIGHT
THROUGH A CHARIOT IN ONE BLOW.
IF WAMUU IS ABLE
TO GET HIS HANDS ON IT,
MY SITUATION
ISN'T JUST GOING TO BE BAD,
IT COULD BE TERMINAL.
BUT IF I CAN GET TO IT FIRST,
COVER IT WITH OIL,
AND FILL IT WITH HAMON,
THEN VICTORY WILL BE MINE.
Wamuu: I AM LOOKING FORWARD TO
AN EXCELLENT, FULFILLING FIGHT
FROM YOU, JOJO. GET READY.
( JoJo gulps )
Kars: THE MOON APPROACHES
THE CLOUD'S EDGE.
WHEN ITS LIGHT FALLS UPON US,
THE CONTEST BEGINS.
( chariot rattles )
Lisa Lisa: JOJO,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE?
THE RACE IS ABOUT TO START.
JoJo: HEH.
I'M WELL AWARE OF THAT.
THE START WILL BE THE KEY, AND I
SURE DON'T WANT TO MESS THAT UP.
THAT'S WHY I'M CHECKING
THE RUBBLE UNDER MY WHEELS.
LOOK AT THAT, WAMUU.
YOU'VE GOT QUITE A BIG PILE
UNDER YOUR BUGGY.
ARE YOU GOING
TO TAKE CARE OF IT?
( Wamuu scoffs )
( JoJo grunts )
Lisa Lisa: HURRY!
COME ON! GET UP THERE!
♪
JOJO!
( JoJo grunts )
Kars: BEGIN NOW!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Kars: BEGIN NOW!
‐ Wamuu: HYAH!
‐ ( horses roar )
JoJo: HYAH!
( Wamuu grunts )
WHAT'S THIS NOW?
Vampire: LORD WAMUU
IS HAVING TROUBLE.
HIS CHARIOT
IS JUST STANDING THERE.
Vampire #2: LOOK AT THAT.
HIS WHEELS ARE BLOCKED.
( Wamuu growls )
JOJO, HE DID THIS.
Lisa Lisa:
THAT CHEEKY LITTLE DEVIL.
Kars: YOU BASTARD.
YOU PILED THEM THERE
WHILE WE TURNED OUR ATTENTION
TO WATCHING THE MOON.
Vampire #3: YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A CHEATER.
Vampire #1:
A ROTTEN HUMAN CHEATER.
( JoJo scoffs )
SHOW ME IN THE HANDBOOK
WHERE IT SAYS I CAN'T DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
ALL YOU TOLD ME WAS
TO LOSE MEANS TO DIE,
AND THAT WAS THE ONLY RULE
IN THIS FIGHT.
WHEN IT COMES TO MY SURVIVAL,
I DON'T CARE WHO I OFFEND.
BEEP BEEP!
Wamuu: HYAH!
( horses neigh )
♪
Vampire #2: THE HUMAN'S
GETTING CLOSE TO THE COLUMN!
Vampire #1: YEAH! GET HIM!
Vampire #3:
DON'T LET HIM GET IT!
( Kars grunts) JOJO WILL BE
THE FIRST ONE TO THE HAMMER.
JoJo: YES, YES, YES, YES!
I CAN'T WAIT
TO HAVE YOU IN MY GRASP.
I'VE GOT YA. YOU'RE MINE.
( gasps )
DAMN, I'M GOING A LOT FASTER
THAN I THOUGHT I WAS.
‐ NO, STAY THERE.
‐ Lisa Lisa: JOJO!
JoJo: EH? IT SNAGGED MY RING.
COULDN'T HAVE PREDICTED THAT.
GREAT. THAT WAS LUCKY.
NOW THE FIGHT IS IN THE BAG.
I'VE GOT THIS.
Wamuu: YOU CAN HAVE THE HAMMER.
THAT WAS MY PLAN
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
( chuckles )
( Kars chuckles )
I SEE WAMUU HAS A PLAN IN MIND.
LET ME SEE IT NOW,
YOUR FIGHTING GENIUS.
JoJo: A LITTLE OIL UP HERE.
ADD SOME HAMON.
I'VE GOT A LITTLE MEDICINE
FOR YOU RIGHT HERE, WAMUU.
Lisa Lisa: WAMUU'S
STARTING TO LOSE SPEED.
Kars: IT'S NOT A RACE.
THEY ARE IN A FIGHT
TO THE DEATH.
THE KEYS TO WINNING
ARE TACTICS AND STRATEGY,
THE RIGHT WEAPONRY,
CONTROL OF THE ENVIRONMENT.
JoJo: ALL RIGHT THEN. I'LL JUST
SLOW DOWN AND INTRODUCE HIM
TO MY LITTLE FRIEND HERE,
THE HAMMER.
Lisa Lisa: JOJO, LISTEN!
YOU MUSTN'T SLOW DOWN ANY MORE!
Wamuu: SINCE YOU'RE
THE ONE WITH THE HAMMER,
I'LL JUST GET SOMETHING ELSE.
( JoJo laughs )
SO, WAMUU, ARE YOU READY TO SEE
EXACTLY WHAT THIS THING CAN DO?
THEN HERE WE GO! HAH‐‐
( both yell )
( vampires laugh )
Vampire #3: LOOK THERE.
HE WAS SO HAPPY
WITH HIS HAMMER AT FIRST,
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
JoJo: HE SURE PLANS AHEAD...
BETTER THAN I DO.
Lisa Lisa: HURRY UP! GO FASTER,
AND GET AWAY FROM HIM, JOJO.
( JoJo gasps )
Wamuu: TOO LATE.
( growls )
( vampire #4 screams )
( JoJo yells )
Wamuu: SO NOW YOU WILL
NO LONGER HAVE YOUR CHARIOT.
( JoJo groans )
( vampires cheer )
Kars: DOWN ALREADY? THINGS SEEM
TO BE OVER A BIT EARLY.
( JoJo groans )
Wamuu: HE MIGHT WANT
TO RETHINK HIS PLAN. HEH.
( JoJo groans )
Lisa Lisa: JOJO!
Wamuu: THE PROBABILITY OF HIM
BEING TRAMPLED
BY MY VAMPIRE HORSES IS 90%,
THE CHANCE OF HIM
ATTEMPTING TO BREAK LEFT IS 5%
AND BREAKING TO THE RIGHT IS 5%.
SO, NOW THEN,
WHAT IS OUR LITTLE HUMAN WARRIOR
GOING TO DO?
JoJo: M‐MY HAMMER.
WHERE IS MY HAMMER?
Vampire #2: HE WANTS HIS HAMMER?
DID HE HIT HIS HEAD TOO HARD?
Vampire #1: THAT HAMMER'S
NOT GOING TO SAVE YOU NOW.
Lisa Lisa: JOJO MUST NOT DODGE.
IF HE DOES, WAMUU WILL STOP
AND FINISH HIM
WITH HIS DIVINE SANDSTORM.
Narrator: BUT WHAT JOJO DID
WAS GRAB THE HAMMER
AND HEAD STRAIGHT
FOR WAMUU'S CHARIOT.
( vampires gasps )
Lisa Lisa: WELL DONE, JOJO.
GREAT THINKING.
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
Vampire #1: WHAT?
Vampire #2: HE STRUCK THE YOKE
MIDWAY BETWEEN THE HORSES!
Narrator: AS THE HORSES RAN ON,
JOJO USED THE HAMMER'S FORCE
TO LAUNCH HIMSELF INTO THE SKY.
( Wamuu gasps )
Kars: HMM?
Vampire #5:
THAT MOVE WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
Vampire #6:
THE HAMMER'S LENGTH KEPT HIM
FROM BEING TRAMPLED
UNDER THE HOOVES OF THE HORSES.
JoJo: HOW WAS THAT?!
( laughs )
AND NOW FOR
THAT BIG HAMMER WHACK
YOU'VE WORKED SO HARD TO EARN.
HUH? WH‐‐
HE'S GONE. W‐WHERE'D HE GO?
Kars: HEH HEH.
YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE
THAT WAMUU IS A STEP
AHEAD OF HIS QUARRY.
( JoJo gasps )
WAIT. THAT'S RIGHT.
THESE FELLAS CAN HIDE THEMSELVES
INSIDE OTHER CREATURES.
( vampires cheer )
( JoJo laughs )
THAT WAS CLOSE.
Vampire #7:
HIS BOOT CAME OFF HIS FOOT.
Vampire #8: THAT BOOT SAVED HIM.
Vampire #9: IF HE ONLY HAD ON
SOME OTHER KIND OF FOOTWEAR.
( Kars scoffs )
JoJo: I'VE GOT LUCK ON MY SIDE,
FOR EXAMPLE, THE WAY
THE HANDLE OF THAT HAMMER
GOT CAUGHT ON MY RING.
LUCK HELPS WITH EFFECTIVENESS.
NOW LET'S TAKE A LOOK
AT YOUR SITUATION.
WAMUU, YOUR OWN POWER
HAS TRAPPED YOU
INSIDE OF THAT HORSE.
THAT'S NOT VERY LUCKY.
( laughs )
AND HERE WE GO!
A LITTLE HAMON FOR YOU
AND THE HORSE YOU RODE IN ON!
Kars: YOU FOOL.
YOU DON'T SEE THE TRAP.
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
CAREFUL, JOJO.
YOU NEED TO KEEP
AT ARM'S LENGTH FROM HIM!
( JoJo gasps )
Kars: NOW THAT WAMUU
HAS MERGED WITH THAT HORSE,
HE'S FREE TO USE HIS HANDS
WITHOUT WORRYING
ABOUT VIBRATION OR SPEED,
WHICH MEANS THAT...
Lisa Lisa: NO ONE HAS SURVIVED
A DIRECT HIT BY THAT ATTACK!
CAESAR COULDN'T.
Wamuu: AND NOW YOU WILL TASTE
DIVINE SANDSTORM!
( JoJo gasps, groans )
( groans )
( vampires cheer )
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
( Kars snaps fingers )
♪
EVEN IF IT LASTED
ONLY THE DISTANCE OF HALF A LAP,
IT WAS A BATTLE FILLED
WITH MANY TWISTS AND SURPRISES.
BUT IN THE END,
WAMUU PROVED THE SUPERIORITY
OF BOTH HIS THINKING
AND HIS FIGHTING PROWESS.
I THINK THE NEXT BATTLE IS GOING
TO BE QUITE A TEST OF WILL.
TRULY, IT IS NOT MY PREFERENCE
TO FIGHT A WOMAN.
WAMUU DISLIKES IT EVEN MORE.
NOTWITHSTANDING, ALL USERS
OF HAMON MUST BE DONE AWAY WITH.
DRINK THAT.
IT WILL PROVIDE
A PAINLESS DEATH.
Lisa Lisa: THANKS.
THAT'S QUITE CONSIDERATE OF YOU,
BUT JOJO SEEMS TO BE A LITTLE
LESS DEAD THAN YOU THOUGHT.
Kars: HUH?
Servant: UH, LORD KARS,
LOOK OUT THERE IN THE ARENA.
Kars: IT CAN'T BE!
Vampire #1: LORD WAMUU'S ARMS,
THEY LOOK LIKE THEY'RE
ABOUT TO FALL OFF.
( Wamuu groans )
MADNESS.
HOW COULD THIS HAVE
POSSIBLY HAPPENED TO ME?
( Lisa Lisa chuckles )
Kars: WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT IS HAPPENING
TO WAMUU OUT THERE?
Vampire #6:
LOOK! THERE, IT'S JOJO.
Vampire #1:
HE'S ALIVE. HE'S MOVING.
Vampire #2: HE'S NOT EVEN HURT.
( JoJo babbles, laughs )
WELL, I APPARENTLY MANAGED
TO SURVIVE ONCE AGAIN.
Kars: BUT WAMUU HIT HIM DIRECTLY
WITH HIS DIVINE
SANDSTORM ATTACK.
HOW COULD HE...
Lisa Lisa: DIRECTLY? HEH.
JOJO WAS CUNNING ENOUGH
TO MAKE IT LOOK
LIKE IT WAS A DIRECT HIT.
HE IS AN ABSOLUTE GENIUS
AT TRICKERY AND MISDIRECTION,
BUT I'M NOT SURE I SHOULD BE
GIVING HIM PRAISE FOR THAT.
Kars: HMM?
Lisa Lisa: TAKE A CLOSE LOOK
AT WAMUU'S ARMS.
♪
Kars: OH. WAIT. NOW I SEE.
HE WRAPPED THE REINS
AROUND WAMUU'S ARMS
AFTER FILLING THEM WITH HAMON.
WAMUU'S DIVINE SANDSTORM
WAS SHORT‐CIRCUITED.
JoJo: WAMUU WAS ALREADY STICKING
ONE HAND OUT OF THE HORSE.
HE WAS GOING TO TRY
TO USE HIS DIVINE SANDSTORM.
HOWEVER, IN ORDER TO DO SO,
I KNEW HE'D HAVE TO STICK
HIS OTHER HAND OUT, TOO,
AND I HAD THE PERFECT COUNTER
FOR THAT MOVE.
Vampire #7:
LORD WAMUU'S FACE, LOOK AT HIM.
Vampire #8:
HE'S IN AGONY. SEE THAT?
Vampire #7: HE DOESN'T SEEM
TO KNOW WHERE HE'S GOING.
HIS EYES ARE VACANT.
Vampire #3:
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
Vampire #2:
IT'S THE SECOND LAP.
Vampire #3:
BUT WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN?
LORD WAMUU CAN'T HOLD
A WEAPON LIKE THAT.
Vampire #2: IS IT EVEN
POSSIBLE FOR HIM TO FIGHT?
Kars: IT'S NOT A SURPRISE.
RIGHT IN MIDATTACK,
WAMUU WAS STRUCK
WITH A LETHAL DOSE OF HAMON.
THE CONFIDENCE BUILT UP
OVER MILLENNIA OF TRIUMPH
HAS CRUMBLED.
THE QUIET, CALM INTENSITY
HIS VICTORIES GAVE HIM
HAS VANISHED.
A TRAGIC SHOCK FOR HIM.
BUT IT MATTERS NOT AT ALL!
PUT OUT THE NEXT SET OF WEAPONS,
AND DO IT NOW!
♪
( Weapon master gasps )
LORD KARS HAS GIVEN THE ORDER.
Weapon master #2:
WHEN HE SPEAKS, WE MUST OBEY.
( both grunt )
Narrator: FOR THE SECOND LAP,
BOTH WARRIORS
WILL RECEIVE CROSSBOWS.
EACH COMES WITH AMMUNITION
FOR TWO SHOTS.
THE FIRST WARRIOR THERE
HAS THE CHOICE
OF THE SMALL OR LARGE BOW.
( weapon masters chuckle )
JoJo: WHAT'S THIS NOW?
THERE'S TWO WEAPONS.
THERE'S A LARGE ONE
AND ANOTHER THAT'S SMALLER.
♪
Kars: LISA LISA,
THIS IS WHAT'S GOING
THROUGH YOUR THOUGHTS NOW.
"WAMUU'S MIND IS IN NO CONDITION
TO ENTERTAIN A FIGHT.
"SO WHY THEN WOULD KARS
BE DEPLOYING THESE NEW WEAPONS
AND WITH
SUCH APPARENT CONFIDENCE?"
IT'S VERY UNSETTLING, IS IT NOT?
WELL, THE REASON IS THAT,
AT HIS CORE,
WAMUU IS A WARRIOR
OF LEGENDARY MENTAL POWER.
Narrator: THE VERY BEST ATHLETES
USE A PSYCHOLOGICAL TECHNIQUE
CALLED THE SWITCH COMEBACK.
WHEN THESE CHAMPIONS
ARE BROUGHT LOW
BY THE PRESSURE
OF SHOCK, FAILURE, OR FEAR,
THEY CAN FLIP A MENTAL SWITCH
AND BRING OUT
THEIR FIGHTING SPIRIT
FOR ONE LAST HERCULEAN EFFORT.
DESPERATE TIMES CALL
FOR DESPERATE MEASURES,
AND WAMUU WILL WIN AT ANY COST.
JoJo: NO, I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
DID HE REALLY JUST DO THAT?
Vampire #1:
WHAT? NO, LORD WAMUU.
Vampire #3:
LOOK! HIS EYES ARE GONE.
Vampires:
HE POKED OUT HIS EYES!
( JoJo gasps )
Wamuu: I FOOLISHLY
RELIED ON MY EYES,
BECAUSE I WAS ABLE TO SEE,
AND JOJO EXPLOITED MY WEAKNESS.
NOW I WILL USE THIS HORN
TO SEE THINGS OUTLINED IN WIND
INSTEAD OF LIGHT.
HYAH!
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
Kars: HE FLIPPED THE SWITCH
BY REMOVING HIS EYES
FROM THE EQUATION.
NOW HE IS ONCE AGAIN
PSYCHOLOGICALLY INVINCIBLE.
HE SENSES THE WIND
WITH THAT HORN ON HIS FOREHEAD.
HE SEES AIR
BETTER THAN HE DID LIGHT.
JoJo: HUH?
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAVE
ANY EFFECT ON ME.
BECAUSE OF YOU,
I LOST MY FRIEND CAESAR.
TRY ANY TRICK YOU WANT.
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO FINISH THE FIGHT.
Weapon master #1: JOJO,
WHICH CROSSBOW WILL YOU TAKE?
Weapon master #2:
YEAH, WHICH ONE?
JoJo: YOU NEED TO ASK?
YOU KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT.
THE LARGE ONE,
YOU STUPID MORONS.
POWER IS WHAT I WANT.
( weapon masters chuckles )
Weapon master #2: YOU GOTTA
ADMIT THAT ONE DOES HAVE POWER.
Weapon master #1:
YEAH, LOTS OF POWER.
( JoJo grunts )
OH, COME ON.
I CAN'T EVEN DRAW THIS THING.
IT'S SO TIGHT.
I CAN'T GET THE STRING
TO GO ANYWHERE AT ALL.
‐ ( weapon masters laugh )
‐ Weapon master #1: YOU LIKE IT?
Weapon master #2:
YOU GOT GREEDY, DIDN'T YA?
EVEN A NORMAL CROSSBOW
TAKES A HUGE AMOUNT OF STRENGTH
TO DRAW BACK. HA HA.
Weapon master #1: YOU HAD
TO HAVE THE BIG ONE, HUH?
Weapon masters:
THAT'S WHAT GREED GETS YOU!
♪
Wamuu: I WILL USE THE FIRST BALL
TO PAINT A PICTURE OF THE WIND.
( JoJo gasps ) WHOA!
Wamuu: NOW THAT I KNOW
WHAT THE RANGE IS,
THE NEXT SHOT WILL NOT MISS.
JoJo: HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO DEFEND MYSELF
IF I CAN'T SHOOT THIS THING?
Vampire #1:
LORD WAMUU, SHOOT HIM!
BLOW HIM TO SMITHEREENS.
Vampire #3: LET US SNACK
ON WHATEVER SMALL PIECES REMAIN.
( JoJo gasps, sighs )
HYAH!
♪
( Wamuu growls )
JoJo: RIGHT. JUST AS I THOUGHT.
THE WIND STIRRED UP
BY THESE FIRES
MAKES IT HARD FOR HIM
TO FIGURE OUT WHERE I AM.
THIS IS THE SPOT.
Kars: THAT'S AN ERROR,
UNDERESTIMATING WAMUU.
( Wamuu growls )
Vampire #10: WHAT? LORD WAMUU'S
POINTING AWAY FROM JOJO.
Vampire #11:
HE'S TURNED THIS WAY.
HE'S AIMING AT US!
( vampires yell )
Kars: JOJO IS STAYING
ON THE OPPOSITE SIDE FROM WAMUU,
THINKING TO SHELTER
BEHIND THE FLAME.
ACTUALLY HE HAS ONLY SERVED
TO POINT OUT HIS POSITION.
Lisa Lisa: I SEE
WHAT WAMUU IS DOING.
HE'S BANKING IT
LIKE IT'S A BILLIARD SHOT.
JoJo: WHAT?!
HE HIT ME FROM BEHIND!
( gags )
♪
( vampires cheer )
‐ ( Kars chuckles )
‐ ( Lisa Lisa gasps )
Wamuu: I WAS
EXAMINING THE TERRAIN
WHILE WE WERE CIRCLING.
I HAD TO FIND
THE PROPER WALL PLACEMENT
TO USE AS A WEAPON.
( JoJo groans )
CAN'T BREATHE.
Kars: THE BALL LOST
SOME OF ITS MOMENTUM,
SO IT DID NOT PIERCE
JOJO'S SKIN.
BUT HE'S SPITTING UP
A LOT OF BLOOD,
WHICH WOULD THEN BETOKEN
SOME INJURY.
FINISH HIM NOW, WAMUU!
BUT REMEMBER HOW WILY
AND FULL OF TRICKS JOJO IS.
BE ON YOUR GUARD!
Wamuu: HAS HE SET ANOTHER TRAP?
( JoJo groaning )
WHEN I HIT THE GROUND,
THE IMPACT COCKED MY CROSSBOW.
I CAN'T LET HIM KNOW THAT.
I CAN'T KILL HIM
FROM THIS DISTANCE.
CLOSER. A LITTLE CLOSER.
THAT'S IT.
Wamuu: HE DID.
( growls )
( JoJo yells )
( gags )
( groans )
( crossbow twangs )
Wamuu: HMM?
( vampires laugh )
Kars: HUH. ALMOST MADE IT.
HIS AIM WAS OFF, THOUGH,
UNFORTUNATELY FOR HIM.
BUT I REALLY MUST COMMEND HIM
FOR STAYING IN THE FIGHT
UNTIL THE VERY LAST.
( chuckles )
( Lisa Lisa gasps )
Wamuu: IT'S OVER, JOJO.
JoJo: NO. STAY AWAY.
OHH. DON'T COME ANY CLOSER.
‐ ( rocks clattering )
‐ GO AWAY. LEAVE ME ALONE.
PLEASE, I JUST
CAN'T TAKE ANY MORE!
YOU'VE GOTTA SPARE ME!
Wamuu: SHAMEFUL.
Vampire #1: LOOK AT HIM.
THE SNIVELING COWARD'S
THROWING ROCKS.
Vampire #3:
HE'S JUST A PATHETIC LOSER.
( vampires booing )
Vampire #2:
TRY TO GO DOWN LIKE A MAN,
YOU DISGUSTING LITTLE WORM!
JoJo: LISTEN, WAMUU.
HERE IS THE VERY NEXT THING THAT
WILL COME OUT OF YOUR MOUTH.
"DON'T YOU DARE DISHONOR
OUR BATTLE HERE, JOJO."
Wamuu: DON'T YOU DARE DISHONOR
OUR BATTLE HERE, JOJO.
( gasps )
JoJo: WANT SOME MORE?
( Wamuu growls )
JoJo: THAT BOTHER YOU?
YOU KNOW THAT A BAT
COULD SIMPLY FLY
RIGHT BETWEEN ALL THOSE ROCKS
AND AVOID EVERY LITTLE PIECE.
WHY CAN'T YOU AVOID THEM
LIKE THAT, WAMUU?
( Wamuu yells )
‐ ( Kars gasps )
‐ Vampire #8: AN IRON BALL!
IT SHOWED UP OUT OF NOWHERE!
Wamuu: YOU BASTARD.
( JoJo laughs )
I GUESS THE HUMAN
JUST TOOK YOU DOWN AGAIN.
YOU SEE, I BANKED THE SHOT
JUST LIKE YOU DID EARLIER.
( wind blowing )
Narrator: THE ARENA WENT SILENT.
NOT ONE INDIVIDUAL MADE A SOUND.
THERE WASN'T EVEN A MOAN.
WAMUU'S INJURY PEERED OUT
LIKE THE SNEERING FACE
OF A JACK‐O'‐LANTERN.
THE IRON BALL CARRIED WITH IT
A SMALL AMOUNT OF HAMON.
THE WOUND BEGAN TO FESTER.
WAMUU'S DAMAGED ARMS
GREW EVEN WORSE.
NO MORE DIVINE SANDSTORMS
NOW OR EVER.
( Wamuu gasps )
( JoJo gasps )
( panting )
I‐I'VE GOT TO TRY
TO BREATHE AGAIN,
GET MY HAMON IN BALANCE.
( Wamuu roars )
JoJo: YOU'RE TRYING A KICK
AFTER FAKING A FALL?
ALL RIGHT. IF YOU STILL
THINK YOU CAN DO THIS.
REBUFF OVERDRIVE!
( Wamuu screams )
Lisa Lisa: IT'S OVER!
WAMUU WON'T BE GETTING UP AGAIN.
( Wamuu shuddering )
HOW CAN THIS BE?
WHAT HAS BECOME
OF THE GREAT WAMUU?
THE MIGHTY WARRIOR IS NO MORE.
12,000 YEARS OF VICTORY
REDUCED TO THIS.
( JoJo grunts )
( gasps ) HIS ARMS.
HIS ARMS ARE GONE.
Wamuu: IT IS NOT WAMUU'S WAY
TO GIVE UP AN EASY WIN.
MY WOUNDS ARE ONLY TO FLESH.
MY LOSSES ARE A PATH TO ABILITY.
I WILL USE ALL OF THESE THINGS
FOR VICTORY!
( JoJo gasps )
Lisa Lisa: HIS ARMS,
HE THREW THEM
USING HIS CHEST WOUND.
THEY GRABBED JOJO
AND ARE CHOKING HIM.
( JoJo grunting )
WHAT'S THIS? I CAN'T BREATHE.
I CAN'T GATHER MY HAMON.
♪
( gasps ) WHAT'S GOING ON?
THAT WIND,
IT'S FLOWING TOWARDS WAMUU.
Wamuu: THE WIND OBEYS ME.
THIS IS MY ULTIMATE MASTERY!
Kars: ULTIMATE MASTERY?
NO, YOU SHOULDN'T!
STOP IT, WAMUU!
IT MUST NOT BE DONE!
JoJo: THE WIND IS GOING
INTO THOSE PIPES.
Wamuu: ULTIMATE MASTERY,
ATMOSPHERIC RIFT!
♪
♪ I WILL REMEMBER YOU
♪ YOUR SILHOUETTE
WILL CHARGE THE VIEW ♪
♪ OF DISTANT ATMOSPHERE
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND EVEN IN THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ DOO DOO DOO, YEAH
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪ ALONG THE DRIFTING CLOUD
♪ THE EAGLE SEARCHING DOWN
ON THE LAND ♪
♪ CATCHING THE SWIRLING WIND
♪ THE SAILOR SEES
THE RIM OF THE LAND ♪
♪ THE EAGLE'S DANCING WINGS
♪ CREATE AS WEATHER
SPINS OUT OF... ♪
♪
Wamuu: YOU COWARDLY ANIMALS!
Kars: NO MATTER
THE METHOD UTILIZED...
Lisa Lisa: REMARKABLE.
JoJo: YOU CROSSED A LINE.
NO HONOR
EARNS YOU NO CONSIDERATION.
Kars: THIS WORLD AND ALL IN IT
BELONG TO ME.