( thunder crashing )
( man laughs )
FEAST YOUR EYES ON THAT WRECK,
WOULD YA?
♪
DAMNATION.
( laughs )
THIS BASTARD MUST'VE DIED
RIGHT QUICKLIKE.
FELL OFF THAT CLIFF,
I'LL WARRANT.
CARRIAGE WHEELS
SLIPPED IN THE MUD.
THEY WEREN'T HURTING FOR COIN,
IF THESE FINE CLOTHES
TELL IT TRUE.
‐ ( baby crying )
‐ Woman: DARIO!
THE LADY IS DEAD,
BUT THE BABY WITH HER,
IT'S STILL ALIVE.
I CAN HEAR IT.
SHE MUST HAVE PROTECTED IT
WITH HER BODY.
Dario: LEAVE IT BE.
SOON ENOUGH, IT'LL BE DEAD.
Woman: W‐WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
Dario: YOU'VE GOT EYES,
AIN'T YA, WOMAN?
I'M APPROPRIATING HIS JEWELRY.
EH? WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
EVIL‐LOOKING THING, AIN'T IT?
WON'T FETCH ME NOTHIN'.
HEY! LEND A HAND!
HELP ME YANK OUT
HIS PEARLY TEETH!
THEY'LL FETCH A PRETTY COPPER.
EH? WHA?!
Man: PROVIDENCE SENDS ME AID
IN THE GUISE OF A MAN.
MANY THANKS.
Dario: EH?
Man: MY WIFE...
MY WIFE AND SON,
TELL ME, DO THEY LIVE?
Dario: I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT YOUR WIFE,
SAINTS PRESERVE HER,
HAS GONE ON
TO HER HEAVENLY REST,
BUT THE BABY IS ALIVE AND WELL.
( man sighs )
FATE IS MOST CRUEL.
MY NAME IS GEORGE JOESTAR.
YOU HAVE SAVED MY LIFE
THIS CURSED NIGHT.
QUICKLY TELL ME YOUR NAME,
THAT I MAY REMEMBER
BEFORE MY SENSES FAIL ME.
( gasps )
( Dario thinking )
THIS PEACOCK THINKS I'M HERE
OUTTA THE GOODNESS OF ME HEART.
HEH HEH HEH HEH HEH.
LITTLE DOES HE KNOW.
HA HA HA HA!
GUESS I'LL OBLIGE HIM!
DARIO BRANDO, YOUR LORDSHIP.
George: SIR, I SWEAR TO YOU,
THE JOESTAR FAMILY WILL HONOR
THE DEBT WE HAVE INCURRED.
♪
( dog barks )
Boy: AH, THERE'S A GOOD BOY.
FATHER! I'M OFF!
George:
THEN FARE THEE WELL, JOJO!
‐ JoJo: LET'S GO, DANNY!
‐ ( Danny barks )
♪
( man coughs )
DIO.
( coughs )
MIND YOUR FATHER.
DAMN YOUR EYES, YOU LAZY BOY.
ARE YOU DEAF?
( Dio sighs )
WHAT DO YOU WANT,
FATHER, MEDICINE?
Dario: YOU IDIOT!
THEIR SNAKE OIL DOES ME NO GOOD.
GET OUT OF HERE,
AND DON'T COME BACK
UNTIL YOU'VE
FOUND ME SOME BOOZE!
♪
George: YOUR MANNERS
ARE DREADFUL.
JoJo: FORGIVE ME, FATHER.
‐ Dio: CHECKMATE.
‐ ( man growls )
TAKE IT.
DON'T FEEL SO SMART NOW,
DO YA, WHELP?
( Dio gasps )
‐ ( boys laughing )
‐ Girl: NO, STOP!
‐ PLEASE, JUST GIVE HER BACK!
‐ Boy: YEAH! YEAH!
Boy #2: OH, LEMME GUESS, ERINA!
YOUR DADDY BOUGHT YOU
THIS DOLL, DIDN'T HE?
IT'S FANCY. BEING A QUACK
MUST PAY HIM REAL NICE.
I KNOW.
WHAT DO YA SAY WE PEEL OFF
THIS FANCY‐LOOKING DRESS, EH,
AND SEE IF THEY MADE HER
WITH ALL
THE REAL GIRL BITS UNDERNEATH?
‐ ( Erina crying )
‐ ( boys laughing )
ERINA'S A CRYBABY!
‐ ERINA'S A CRY‐‐
‐ JoJo: THAT'S ENOUGH!
GIVE IT BACK TO HER RIGHT NOW!
Boy #2: WHO'S THIS GUY?
Boy #1: YOU SOME FRIEND
OF ERINA'S?
JoJo: I'VE NEVER MET HER,
BUT I'LL FIGHT FOR HER
ALL THE SAME!
Boy #1: WHO IS THIS IDIOT?
GETTING IN A FIGHT
FOR A GIRL HE DON'T EVEN KNOW!
( JoJo gasps )
Boy #2: LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY
WAS NOTHIN' BUT TALK.
( both laugh )
Boy #1: LOOK AT HIM
THERE ON THE GROUND.
ARE YOU GONNA CRY?
SOME KNIGHT IN SHINING ARMOR
YOU TURNED OUT TO BE.
( JoJo gasping )
Boy #1: HUH? THIS LITTLE
PANTYWAIST IS THE JOESTAR KID.
NOW THAT I KNOW
YOU'RE SOME RICH GUY'S SON,
WE'RE JUST GETTING STARTED.
YOU CAN'T
BUY YOUR WAY OUTTA THIS.
( blows striking )
Boy #2: HIT HIM SOME MORE!
Dario: LISTEN, DIO.
I AM NOT LONG FOR THIS WORLD.
WHEN I DIE‐‐( coughs )
YOU GET YOURSELF
TO THE JOESTAR MANSION
ALONG WITH THIS LETTER.
THE FOOL THINKS HE OWES ME.
THIS IS
YOUR TICKET TO GREATNESS.
IT'S YOUR ONLY CHANCE, DIO.
GO OUT THERE,
AND TAKE THIS USELESS WORLD
FOR ALL YOU CAN GET.
( JoJo groans )
( boy #1 spits )
CRAWL ON BACK
TO YOUR DAMN MANOR,
LITTLE LORD FAUNTLEROY.
Boy #2: LET'S GO.
( JoJo groaning )
Erina: YOU OKAY?
JoJo: JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
I'LL BE FINE!
I DID NOT TAKE A BEATING
JUST NOW FOR YOUR SAKE,
SO WHATEVER
YOU'RE THINKING, STOP IT!
ALL I WANT IS TO CONDUCT MYSELF
AS A GENTLEMAN.
I SPOTTED A DAMSEL IN DISTRESS.
A TRUE GENTLEMAN HAS NO FEAR.
HE'LL FIGHT FOR THOSE WHO CAN'T.
EVEN KNOWING IT'S A FIGHT
HE HAS NO CHANCE OF WINNING,
HE ENTERS THE FRAY.
SOMEDAY, I'LL HAVE
THE STRENGTH TO WIN.
( bird squawking )
Dio: DEVIL THAT YOU WERE,
YOU DROVE MOTHER
TO AN EARLY GRAVE.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE DEAD.
MAY YOU BURN FOR YOUR SINS.
THE RICHES
THAT ELUDED YOUR GRASP,
I WILL CLAIM THEM IN EXCESS.
YOU LACKED THE CUNNING
TO TAKE WHAT YOU WANTED,
BUT I'LL PREVAIL.
THIS JOESTAR SHALL BE THE KEY.
NOW BURN. ( spits )
♪
I WILL CLAIM
WHAT IS RIGHTFULLY MINE.
Erina: "JONATHAN JOESTAR."
Narrator: THIS IS THE TALE
OF TWO YOUNG MEN,
THEIR DESTINIES
BOUND TO INTERSECT,
AND THE STONE MASK THAT CHANGES
THEIR FATES FOREVER.
( hoofbeats )
( horses neighing )
( chorus vocalizes )
( JoJo thinking ) WHO IS HE?
YOU MUST BE DIO BRANDO, RIGHT?
Dio: AND YOU'RE JONATHAN,
HEIR TO THE JOESTARS.
JoJo: YES. PLEASE, CALL ME JOJO.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
( Danny barking )
JoJo: DANNY!
( laughs )
THAT'S DANNY. HE'S MY DOG,
AS WELL
AS MY STEADFAST COMPANION.
DON'T WORRY. HE KNOWS BETTER
THAN TO NIP AT STRANGERS.
( Dio scoffs )
( Danny yelps )
( JoJo gasps )
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?!
HOW DARE YOU?!
Dio: SO THIS IS
THE BRAT I MUST USURP.
WEARS HIS HEART ON HIS SLEEVE.
HE'S QUICK TO ANGER.
THIS PAMPERED FOOL IS NO MATCH
FOR THE LIKES OF DIO BRANDO.
George: FIGHTING ALREADY?
( JoJo gasps )
George: I WOULD KNOW
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
Dio: SORRY.
THE DOG JUMPED AT ME,
AND IN MY HASTE, I STRUCK IT.
( chuckles )
George: WELCOME TO THE MANOR.
CONSIDER YOURSELF
A PART OF THE FAMILY.
EVERYONE,
I WOULD HAVE DIED IN THE CRASH
THAT CLAIMED MY WIFE
WERE IT NOT FOR DIO'S FATHER.
YOU WILL TREAT HIM
AS YOU WOULD MY OWN SON.
Butler: VERY WELL,
YOUR LORDSHIP.
George: THIS IS
YOUR HOME NOW, DIO.
PLEASE AVAIL YOURSELF
OF ALL ITS COMFORTS.
Dio: THANK YOU, SIR,
FOR TAKING IN
THIS POOR UNFORTUNATE.
George: JOJO HAS LOST
HIS MOTHER AS WELL,
AND YOU'RE THE SAME AGE.
YOU'LL BE THICK AS THIEVES SOON.
JOJO, DIO DIDN'T MEAN
TO HURT DANNY.
JoJo: RIGHT.
IT STANDS TO REASON, FATHER.
IF A STRANGE DOG JUMPED AT ME,
I'D BE SURPRISED, TOO.
I WISH HIS APOLOGY
HAD BEEN MORE SINCERE,
BUT AS WE'LL BE
LIVING HERE TOGETHER,
I'LL DO MY UTMOST
TO BE FRIENDLY.
George: THIS WAY, DIO.
I'LL SHOW YOU YOUR CHAMBER.
Dio: YES, SIR.
( JoJo yelps )
YOU'RE HURTING ME!
‐ PLEASE LET GO.
‐ Dio: WATCH YOUR HANDS.
NO ONE'S ALLOWED TO TOUCH
MY THINGS WITHOUT MY PERMISSION.
( JoJo gasps )
Dio: NEXT TIME YOU REACH
FOR WHAT'S MINE WITH THIS PAW,
I'LL BREAK IT.
JoJo: I WAS ONLY TRYING TO HELP!
‐ Dio: WELL, DON'T.
‐ ( JoJo gasping )
I WILL HAVE A SERVANT
CARRY THEM UP FOR ME.
LISTEN. I MAY BE
A GUEST WITHIN YOUR HOUSE,
BUT I AM NOT TO BE TRIFLED WITH.
IN ALL THINGS THAT I DO,
I AM NUMBER ONE.
LOOK DOWN YOUR NOSE AT ME,
AND YOU'LL REGRET IT.
JoJo: BUT, DIO,
I WANT FOR US TO BE FRIENDS.
Dio: AND ANOTHER THING.
I HATE ALL MONGRELS.
THEY DON'T SCARE ME.
I JUST DESPISE HOW THEY
FAWN OVER THE UNWORTHY.
SO KEEP THAT MANGY MUTT OF YOURS
WELL AWAY FROM ME, JOESTAR.
George: DIO, WHAT'S KEEPING YOU?
HURRY ALONG.
Dio: YES, SIR.
Narrator: WITH DIO'S
SUDDEN ARRIVAL,
JOJO'S CAREFREE LIFE
SPIRALED INTO ONE OF MISERY.
( JoJo yelps )
George: YOU GOT
ANOTHER ONE WRONG, JOJO!
LOOK AT DIO. 20 OUT OF 20,
NOT A SINGLE MISTAKE.
( JoJo gasps )
JOJO!
YOUR TABLE MANNERS
ARE SIMPLY ABHORRENT.
YOU ACT AS IF
YOU WERE RAISED IN A BARN.
( snaps fingers )
CLEAR JOJO'S PLATE AT ONCE.
‐ HE'S HAD ENOUGH.
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
George: THAT'S ALL THE DINNER
YOU GET TONIGHT.
IT'S CLEAR TO ME THAT I
FAILED IN YOUR UPBRINGING
WHEN I LOOK AT DIO.
IF YOUR MOTHER
COULD SEE YOU NOW.
DIO'S MANNERS ARE IMPECCABLE.
( JoJo sighs )
( sputtering )
( Dio scoffs ) WHAT AN OAF.
( men cheering )
Host: OUR FIRST PUGILIST UP
IS JONATHAN JOESTAR.
( crowd cheers )
Host: HE'S BEEN LOOKING
STRONGER LATELY, I'D SAY.
AS FOR HIS OPPONENT TODAY,
IT'S A BOXER
WE HAVEN'T SEEN BEFORE.
JoJo: HUH?
Host: HE'S A NEWCOMER
TO OUR FAIR CITY.
‐ ALL WE KNOW IS HIS NAME.
‐ Man: I WONDER HOW HE'LL DO.
JoJo: IT CAN'T BE.
♪
Host: INTRODUCING
OUR SURPRISE OPPONENT,
DIO BRANDO!
SAME AS EVER. LAND A HIT
TO THE OTHER GUY'S FACE,
AND THE MATCH IS OVER.
NOW FIGHT.
‐ ( bell rings )
‐ ( crowd cheering )
Man: GET HIM, JOJO!
Man #2: TAKE HIM DOWN!
Man #3: LOOK AT HIM
DODGE THOSE HITS.
Man #1: I'VE NEVER
SEEN THE LIKE.
JoJo: I CAN'T CONNECT.
Dio: THE PAMPERED BRAT CAN BOX.
I'LL GRANT HIM THAT MUCH.
HOWEVER...
( JoJo gasps )
Dio: HE'S NEVER
HAD TO PUNCH HIS WAY OUT
OF A SCRAPE IN THE SLUMS,
AND THUS I HOLD THE ADVANTAGE.
TAKE THIS.
Host: THERE IT IS!
JOJO LOSES THE FIGHT.
Dio: YOUR SUFFERING
ISN'T OVER YET, JOJO.
I'LL JAM A THUMB INTO YOUR EYE
FOR GOOD MEASURE,
LEST YOU FORGET
WHO YOU'RE DEALING WITH.
( crowd cheering )
Man #2: THAT ARM
OF HIS IS UNREAL.
Man #3: DIO!
Man #4: DIO, THAT PUNCH
WAS SIMPLY AMAZING!
Man #1: HOW DID YOU
DODGE HIM SO WELL?
Dio: IT'S JUST
A LITTLE DEFENSIVE FOOTWORK
I ACQUIRED ALONG THE WAY.
IF YOU'D LIKE TO LEARN IT,
I'D BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO TEACH IT TO YOU FELLAS.
Man #1: YOU WOULD DO THAT?
Dio: DO TAKE CARE
THAT NOBODY SHOWS IT TO JOJO.
HE CAN'T KEEP A SECRET
TO SAVE HIS LIFE.
Man #3: YOU DON'T SAY.
Man #2: THANKS FOR THE WARNING.
JoJo: THE THUMB IN MY EYE...
THAT WAS ON PURPOSE.
♪
Dio: LONELINESS WILL DEVOUR
A MAN FROM WITHIN.
I'LL REDUCE JOJO
TO AN EMPTY HUSK.
BIT BY DEVIOUS BIT, I'LL STEAL
THE LIFE HE WAS MEANT TO HAVE.
BY THE TIME WE'RE GROWN,
THERE'LL BE
NOTHING LEFT OF HIM.
♪
JoJo: DAMN THAT DIO.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
HE'S RUINING
EVERYTHING HE TOUCHES.
‐ Boy: LOOK ALIVE, FELLAS.
‐ JoJo: EH?
HEY! IT'S ME, JONATHAN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
MIND IF I JOIN YOU?!
Boy: HUH.
I COULD HAVE SWORN
I HEARD A VOICE A MOMENT AGO.
Boy #2: JUST THAT SNITCH.
BETTER TO IGNORE 'EM.
JoJo: WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I'M A SNITCH, HUH?
CALL ME THAT TO MY FACE!
Boy #3: TIME TO GO.
Boy #1: JOJO'S NOTHING
BUT A SNITCH.
DIO WAS RIGHT ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE JUST A STUPID
RICH‐BOY TATTLETALE!
JoJo: TELL ME WHAT I
SNITCHED ABOUT, THEN!
HE'S LYING TO YOU!
WHY DO YOU
JUST TAKE HIM AT HIS WORD?!
Boys: JOJO THE SQUEALER!
( laughing )
JoJo: DIO, HE'S SLANDERING ME.
HE LIES AND LIES,
AND PEOPLE JUST EAT IT UP!
FROM THE FIRST DAY HE SHOWED UP,
HE'S BEEN TRYING TO DESTROY ME.
DAMN YOU, DIO BRANDO!
DIO! DIO! DIO! DIO!
EVER SINCE HE ARRIVED,
EVERYONE'S TURNED ON ME,
EVEN FATHER.
( Danny whimpers )
JoJo: OH, DANNY,
I KNOW YOU WILL
ALWAYS BE MY FRIEND,
NO MATTER WHAT DIO DOES.
( Danny whimpers )
EH?
HUH?
WHO WAS THAT GIRL JUST NOW?
I FEEL AS THOUGH
I HAVE SEEN HER FACE BEFORE.
( gasps )
THAT'S MY HANDKERCHIEF.
SHE BROUGHT GRAPES.
HEY, THANK YOU FOR THE FRUIT!
YOU KNOW, I'LL BE HERE TOMORROW
IF YOU WANT TO COME BACK.
( chuckles )
DIDN'T EVEN TELL ME HER NAME.
JUST RAN AWAY.
GIRLS ARE SUCH A CURIOUS BUNCH.
( riders screaming )
Narrator: A DARK TIME
IN JONATHAN'S LIFE
WAS SUDDENLY MADE BRIGHTER
BY LOVE'S GROWING EMBERS.
THE TWO BECAME FAST FRIENDS,
AND JONATHAN
WAS ENCHANTED BY HER.
JoJo: ERINA PENDLETON.
THE NAME IS MUSIC TO MY EARS.
‐ JoJo: TAKE THIS!
‐ ( voice‐over ) SHE'S AN ANGEL.
Erina: WHAT ON EARTH
ARE YOU DOING TO THAT POOR TREE?
JOJO! WHAT POSSESSED YOU
TO DO THAT?
GOODNESS.
JoJo: FAREWELL, ERINA,
'TIL NEXT TIME.
( Danny barks )
♪
( Dio chuckles )
( Erina sighs )
( gasps ) HUH?
Dio: YOUR NAME WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO BE ERINA, WOULD IT?
YOU AND JOJO, YOU MAKE
SUCH A SMART‐LOOKING COUPLE.
REALLY, I SHOULD HAVE
GUESSED AS MUCH.
TRY AS I MIGHT TO RUIN HIS LIFE,
YOUNG MASTER JONATHAN
HAS BEEN ODDLY HAPPY AS OF LATE.
( Erina gasps )
( gasps )
Boys: HE‐‐HE DID IT!
( Erina grunting )
Boy: GIVE HER THE WHAT‐FOR!
THE TROUBLE I'D GET INTO
IF I WERE AS BRAVE AS DIO.
HE JUST DOES WHAT HE WANTS,
DEVIL MAY CARE.
( Erina gasps )
Dio: TELL ME,
HAVE YOU AND JOJO KISSED YET?
I'LL TAKE THAT AS A NO.
YOU THOUGHT YOUR FIRST KISS
WOULD BE JOJO,
BUT IT WAS I, DIO.
( Erina gasps )
Dio: EVEN THOUGH
IT WAS BY FORCE,
THE FACT THAT I KISSED HER
IS ENOUGH.
I'VE KILLED THEIR ROMANCE
BEFORE IT BEGAN.
I'LL DENY JOJO THE COMFORT
OF FRIENDSHIP AND LOVE.
Boy: WHAT THE?
JUST LOOK AT HER, DIO.
SHE'S TAKEN LEAVE
OF HER SENSES.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
Boy #2: WASHING OUT HER MOUTH
WITH A MUDDY PUDDLE?
Boy #1: WHY WOULD
ANYBODY DO THAT?
THERE'S A STREAM NOT FAR AWAY.
( Dio scoffs )
YOU UNGRATEFUL WENCH!
YOU DARE SUGGEST MY KISS
IS SOMETHING TO BE WASHED OFF!
( Erina gasps )
Dio: COOL YOUR TEMPER,
YOU DAMNABLE FOOL.
SHE'S NOT WORTH
LOSING YOUR HEAD OVER.
WE'RE DONE HERE. COME ON.
Boy #1: HUH?
JoJo: EH? ERINA!
HEY THERE.
( Erina crying )
JoJo: AHH?
ERINA, WAIT!
WHY'D SHE RUN OFF?
WAS IT SOMETHING I SAID?
( boys laughing )
Boy #1: LOOK AT HIM, FELLAS.
HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHY SHE RAN AWAY.
Boy #3: WHAT DO YA SAY
WE TELL HIM?
HE DESERVES TO KNOW WHAT
HIS PRECIOUS ERINA'S BEEN UP TO.
Boy #1: I DUNNO.
I'D FEEL BAD MAKING HIS
LITTLE LORDSHIP START TO CRY.
( JoJo sputters )
THIS IS HIS DOING.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE, DIO?
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE
TO MY ERINA?!
( screams )
DIO!
Dio: HUSH, BOY.
YOU WON'T SPEAK MY NAME
IN VAIN AGAIN
IF YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD FOR YOU.
Dio: WE END THIS NOW!
I WON'T LET YOU SULLY
AN INNOCENT MAIDEN'S HONOR!
YOUR FIGHT IS WITH ME, DAMN IT!
Dio: UPSET ABOUT ERINA,
THAT SHE SHARED
HER FAVORS WITH ME?
AND NOW YOU INTEND TO GIVE ME
A PROPER THRASHING
FOR MY IMPUDENCE.
JoJo: THIS TIME, DIO,
YOU HAVE GONE TOO FAR!
Dio: YOU MAY BE RIGHT,
BUT YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'LL PAY!
LOOKING TO REPEAT
YOUR PERFORMANCE
FROM OUR BOXING MATCH?
BE MY GUEST.
HUMPH.
( JoJo sputters )
I CAN'T BEAT HIM,
BUT IF I LOSE HERE AND NOW,
I'LL SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE
COWERING IN DIO'S SHADOW.
MOST OF ALL, I HAVE TO FIGHT
FOR ERINA'S HONOR.
SHE NEEDS A CHAMPION!
Dio: TIME TO END
THIS LITTLE PISSING MATCH.
I'LL BEAT HIM HERE,
IN HIS OWN HOME.
ONCE AND FOR ALL,
HE'LL KNOW HIS PROPER PLACE
IN THIS WORLD IS UNDER MY HEEL.
HE'LL SEE THAT IT'S USELESS
TO TRY AND DEFEAT ME.
I SHALL BE MASTER,
NOW AND ALWAYS.
( JoJo screaming )
Dio: COME ON!
PERFECT. RIGHT IN THE FACE.
HOW ARE YOU ABLE TO GRAB ME
AFTER SUCH A BLOW TO THE HEAD?!
PERHAPS I WAS
TOO GENTLE WITH YOU!
( Dio gags )
JoJo: DIO!
Dio: IMPOSSIBLE.
JoJo: I'M GOING TO BEAT YOU
‐ 'TIL YOU CRY LIKE A BABY, DIO!
‐ Dio: IMPOSSIBLE!
HOW COULD A PAMPERED BRAT
LIKE HIM BEST ME IN A FIGHT?
♪
JoJo: EH?
Dio: Y‐YOU...
HOW‐‐HOW DARE YOU?
BASTARD,
HOW DARE YOU STRIKE ME?!
JoJo: DIO'S CRYING.
Dio: I'LL MAKE YOU REGRET THAT,
YOU FILTHY CUR!
George: STOP IT, BOTH OF YOU!
THAT IS QUITE ENOUGH.
JoJo: FATHER, I‐‐
George: SON, I KNOW
THAT BOYS YOUR AGE
ARE PRONE TO FISTICUFFS.
HOWEVER, JOJO, I SAW YOU
PUMMEL DIO MERCILESSLY
AFTER THE POINT
AT WHICH HE HAD
OBVIOUSLY NO CHANCE
OF WINNING THE FIGHT.
‐ SUCH IS THE MARK OF A COWARD.
‐ JoJo: FATHER!
George: NO EXCUSES.
TO YOUR CHAMBERS, BOTH OF YOU.
( JoJo sputters )
George: I'LL DECIDE
YOUR PUNISHMENT ANON.
( gardener grunts )
HMM. THAT SEEMS STRANGE.
WONDER WHAT'S IN THERE.
OH, WELL.
PROBABLY SOMETHING
A MAID THREW OUT.
HMM?
( thumping )
W‐WHAT'S THAT?
SOMETHING GOT
INTO THE INCINERATOR.
OH, MERCY!
WHAT‐‐WHAT IF
A PERSON'S IN THERE?
THEY'RE BURNING ALIVE,
AND IT'S ALL MY FAULT
FOR LIGHTING IT!
♪
ERINA.
DAMN YOU, DIO!
I BEAT YOU FAIR AND SQUARE,
BUT WHAT DOES IT MATTER,
IF YOU'VE RUINED THINGS
FOR ERINA AND ME?
George: WE BURIED HIM
WHILE YOU WERE GONE, SON.
IT WAS NOTHING
YOU SHOULD HAVE TO WITNESS.
THE CONSTABLE SAID IT WAS
PROBABLY THE WORK OF A BURGLAR
WHO CAUGHT SIGHT OF DANNY
AND PANICKED.
JoJo: DIO.
Butler: HE'S NOT HERE.
HE HASN'T YET RETURNED
FROM SCHOOL TODAY, SIR.
Narrator: JOJO FLED TO HIS ROOM
AND FELL
INTO A DREAMLESS SLUMBER.
WHEN HE AWOKE,
HE THOUGHT OF DANNY,
HIS LOYAL PET
AND ONE TRUE FRIEND,
NOW LOST TO HIM, AND WEPT.
Dio: YES, I MAY HAVE EVENED
THE SCORE BY KILLING HIS MUTT,
BUT IT DOESN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT JOJO IS FAR STRONGER
THAN I'D THOUGHT.
BLOODY HIS NOSE, AND HE
COMES BACK TWICE AS FIERCE.
MY ANGER MAKES ME VULNERABLE.
I MUST REMEDY THAT.
ONCE I LEARN
TO MASTER MY TEMPER,
I'LL BE INVINCIBLE
TO THE LIKES OF JOJO.
Narrator:
IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE,
SEVEN YEARS PASSED.
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
Narrator: SEVEN YEARS LATER...
Commentator: THE BALL IS PLUCKED
OUT OF THE AIR BY OUR HERO.
JoJo: HAVING READ IT,
ALL HAS BEEN MADE CLEAR.
Man: IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO LOSE
BODY PARTS, DO STICK AROUND.
‐ Dio: WE ARE FRIENDS NO MORE!
‐ JoJo: YOU HURT FATHER.
NEVER AGAIN, DIO!