( wind blowing )
♪
Tonpetty: FOR THREE YEARS,
YOU HAVE ENDURED
AND SURVIVED OUR TRAINING.
YOU CAN RUN
FOR UNIMAGINABLE DISTANCES
AND NOT BE SHORT OF BREATH.
SOON YOU WILL BE READY TO BEGIN
THE INTENSE TRAINING
THAT WE CALL THE CELESTIAL GATE.
BUT I WARN YOU AGAIN, ZEPPELI,
IF YOUR CHOICE IS TO CONTINUE
WITH THESE TEACHINGS,
YOU WILL BE SEALING YOUR FATE.
THE TIME TO TURN BACK IS NOW.
YOU'RE YOUNG.
YOU CAN START A NEW LIFE.
Zeppeli: MASTER TONPETTY,
READ THE WAVES OF MY LIFE.
TELL ME HOW LONG I HAVE.
WHEN IS THIS LIFE OF MINE
GOING TO END?
WHERE DOES IT END?
HOW DOES IT END?
Tonpetty: WHY DO YOU WANT
THIS KNOWLEDGE?
Zeppeli: I BELIEVE THERE IS
A PURPOSE TO MY LIFE,
ONE THAT I CANNOT SET ASIDE.
I NEED TO KNOW
SO I CAN FULFILL THAT PURPOSE.
IF I KNOW HOW MUCH TIME
I HAVE TO ACCOMPLISH IT,
THEN I CAN ACCEPT THE OUTCOME.
I WILL ACCEPT IT.
Zeppeli: SO LET IT BE DONE,
IF THAT IS WHAT YOU BELIEVE.
KNOW THIS.
♪
( Zeppeli grunts )
IN AN ANCIENT CHAMBER,
HIDDEN FROM THE LIGHT
AND REEKING OF DEATH,
A CHILD
SHALL OPEN THE WAY FOR YOU.
TO UNCHAIN A YOUNG LION
AND RELEASE HIM
INTO THE FUTURE OF HIS DESTINY,
YOU WILL BURN YOUR OWN WOUNDS.
THEN FREELY
WILL YOU OPEN YOUR ARMS
TO THE CRUEL DEATH
THAT AWAITS YOU.
‐ ( JoJo grunts )
‐ ( Tarukus growls )
Speedwagon: BARON ZEPPELI,
BE CAREFUL, MY FRIEND.
( Zeppeli breathes deeply )
HERE I COME, JOJO.
♪
"TO UNCHAIN A YOUNG LION
AND RELEASE HIM INTO
THE FUTURE OF HIS DESTINY..."
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( JoJo gasping )
CAN'T BUDGE THIS COLLAR.
STRANGE.
FOR SOME REASON,
TARUKUS HASN'T MADE A DISPLAY
OF HIS TRICKS
FOR FIGHTING IN THIS ROOM.
THAT WORRIES ME.
Tarukus: COME TO ME, FOOLS.
YOU THINK YOUR HAMON
WILL DO ANY GOOD?
YOU LITTLE BUGS
CAN'T LAY A FINGER ON ME,
NO MATTER HOW HARD YOU MAY TRY!
HUH?
YOU AFRAID?
GONNA SOIL YOURSELF?!
♪
‐ ( chain rattles )
‐ ( Tarukus growls )
Speedwagon:
MASTERFULLY PLAYED, BARON.
( Tarukus roars )
Zeppeli: HERE WE GO!
HOW ABOUT THIS?!
TORNADO OVERDRIVE!
JoJo: WATCH YOUR BACK!
Zeppeli:
HE'S ATTACKING FROM ABOVE?
JoJo: NO, ZEPPELI!
HE'S COMING FROM BELOW!
( Zeppeli grunts )
Tarukus: WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE BOTH RIGHT.
( Zeppeli gasps )
Tarukus: I CALL IT
"HELL HEAVEN SNAKE KILL."
( Zeppeli groans )
( Speedwagon gasps )
( JoJo gagging )
( Tarukus laughs )
LOVELY WATCHING YOU SUFFOCATE.
Zeppeli: I‐‐I CAN'T BREATHE.
MY HAMON WON'T MANIFEST.
( Tarukus growls )
( Speedwagon screams )
( gasping )
Zeppeli: JO‐‐
JOJO...
( groans )
( chain rattles )
( Tarukus grunts )
♪
LORD DIO, AS YOU ORDERED,
THEY'RE DEAD, BOTH OF THEM.
( Speedwagon gasps )
THIS IS‐‐
THIS BLOODY SAVAGERY
IS UNBELIEVABLE!
( gasps )
( wails )
( JoJo gasping )
Tarukus: HMM?
( grunts )
( Speedwagon gasps )
JONATHAN!
( JoJo groaning )
( Tarukus growls )
EVEN WITH A BROKEN NECK,
YOU HAVE THE POOR TASTE
TO STILL BE ALIVE?
ALLOW ME TO FINISH YOU OFF.
( growls )
Zeppeli: JO‐‐
JOJO.
( Tarukus grunts )
LIVELY FOR ONLY HALF A MAN.
Zeppeli: FREELY I GIVE THIS.
FREELY I GIVE THIS.
FREELY I GIVE THIS TO YOU!
MY ULTIMATE TECHNIQUE!
JOJO, TAKE IT!
MAKE IT YOURS!
( heart beating )
ULTIMATE DEEP PASS OVERDRIVE!
( JoJo gasps )
( screams )
( Zeppeli screams )
( Speedwagon gasping )
Zeppeli: DONE.
JOJO, I HAVE PASSED ON TO YOU
ALL THE HAMON WHICH WAS MINE
TO CONTROL IN THIS LIFE.
( Speedwagon gasping )
GO, DEAR FRIEND.
GO.
BARON ZEPPELI!
‐ ( wailing )
‐ ( footsteps thudding )
Tarukus: A TOUCHING DISPLAY,
BUT I'M STILL GOING
TO GRIND YOU INTO RED PAS‐‐
( gags )
♪
Tarukus: YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
Speedwagon: WHAT?
HE HAULED TARUKUS OFF THE GROUND
LIKE A SACK OF TURNIPS.
IT'S AS IF THE BARON'S HAMON
HEALED HIS BROKEN NECK.
‐ ( JoJo grunting )
‐ Tarukus: NUMSKULL.
YOU ACTUALLY THINK
YOU CAN YANK THAT COLLAR OPEN?
YOU PATHETIC WASTE OF FLESH.
I COULDN'T PULL APART
THOSE STEEL BANDS,
EVEN WITH ALL THE POWER
GIVEN TO ME BY LORD DIO.
( JoJo grunting )
OH, NO, TARUKUS?!
Speedwagon: JONATHAN!
( Tarukus groans )
YOU BUG, HOW'D‐‐
JoJo: TWISTED BY MADNESS.
NO HUMAN FEELING.
YOU GAVE UP YOUR REDEMPTION
WHEN YOU CHOSE
TO FOLLOW DIO, TARUKUS.
( Tarukus chuckles )
( roars )
( JoJo breathes deeply )
( yells )
( Tarukus grunts )
( screams )
Speedwagon: LOOK AT THAT.
HIS HAMON'S VISIBLE.
HIS BODY CAN BARELY
CONTAIN ITS STRENGTH.
THE BARON'S HAMON JOINED
AND MULTIPLIED INCREDIBLY
WITH JONATHAN'S.
THERE'S BEEN NOTHING
LIKE THIS EVER!
JoJo: TARUKUS, YOU CANNOT
BE ALLOWED TO CONTINUE.
THIS IS CLEAR.
YOUR EVIL SPIRIT
MUST BE BANISHED!
( Tarukus growls )
( fangs crack )
JoJo: YOUR TIME IS DONE.
NOW I'LL ERASE YOU!
Tarukus: ENOUGH OF YOUR BLATHER.
YOU TALK TOO MUCH!
( spits )
( roaring )
JoJo: YOU'LL HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT!
( yelling )
Speedwagon: WELL PLAYED!
♪
JoJo: BARON ZEPPELI!
SPEAK TO ME.
( Zeppeli gasping )
JoJo: THIS IS ALL
SO TERRIBLY WRONG.
WITHOUT YOU BESIDE ME,
WITHOUT YOUR WISDOM
AND GUIDANCE,
HOW WILL I MAKE MY WAY
THROUGH THIS WORLD?
( Zeppeli gasps )
JOJO, YOU SIMPLY
MUST PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
YOU'VE NO TIME TO WASTE NOW.
( gasps )
YOU KNOW WHAT LIES AHEAD.
NOW GO. LEAVE ME.
SETTLE ACCOUNTS WITH DIO.
BUT FIRST OF ALL,
YOU MUST DESTROY THE MASK.
‐ ( gags )
‐ JoJo: ZEPPELI!
( Poco crying )
Zeppeli: PLEASE DON'T CRY.
NO TEARS.
I AM SATISFIED.
I HAVE LIVED MY DESTINY.
WHEN I WAS YOUNG,
I WAS VERY HAPPILY MARRIED,
BUT TO PURSUE THE MASK,
I LEFT MY FAMILY BEHIND.
HOWEVER, I'VE NEVER REGRETTED
THE CHOICE I MADE.
I ACCEPT IT COMPLETELY.
AND IT'S GOOD.
IN THE END, I CAN SEE
THAT MY CHOICE
WAS THE RIGHT ONE.
JOJO, YOU ARE MY DELIVERANCE.
BARON ZEPPELI.
( Zeppeli chuckles )
IT SEEMS TO ME THAT IN YOU
I HAVE FOUND BOTH
A BEST FRIEND AND A NEW FAMILY.
JOJO, THROUGH YOU,
I WILL LIVE ON FOREVER.
MY SON...
JOJ‐‐
( both gasp )
♪
Narrator:
THE 19th‐CENTURY NOVELIST
WILLIAM MAKEPEACE THACKERAY
WROTE...
"TO LOVE AND WIN
IS THE BEST THING."
"TO LOVE AND LOSE
IS THE NEXT BEST."
AND SO IT WAS THAT JOJO
TOOK UP HIS MENTOR'S LIFE QUEST
AS WELL AS HIS SPIRIT.
♪
JoJo: FAREWELL, MY FRIEND.
( woman sobs )
OH, PLEASE, SIR.
I BEG YOU, PLEASE DON'T
BRING NO HARM TO MY CHILD.
LET HIM BE.
( gasps )
Dio: HMM.
DO I COMPREHEND YOU?
LET US CLARIFY WHAT YOU DESIRE.
VOLUNTARILY YOU WILL
GIVE YOURSELF TO US
ON THE CONDITION
THAT WE NOT TOUCH YOUR CHILD.
IS THAT ACCURATE?
( zombies growling )
Woman: YES.
ONLY DON'T HURT MY BOY.
Dio: YOU MOVE ME TO TEARS.
AGREED.
YOU SHALL HAVE YOUR WISH.
I HEREBY SWEAR THAT NEITHER I
NOR ANY OF MY SERVANTS
WILL BRING HARM TO YOUR CHILD.
THAT SAID, YOU NEED
TO BE AWARE OF ONE THING.
ALL MY MINIONS,
WITHOUT EXCEPTION,
WILLINGLY GAVE UP
THEIR SOULS FOR ME.
I TRULY THINK
IT WOULD WORK OUT FAR BETTER
IF BOTH OF YOU WERE TO JOIN ME.
THERE WOULD BE NO MORE WORRIES.
YOU WOULD BOTH BE PART
OF A NEW AND GREATER FAMILY.
Woman: REMEMBER, YOU PROMISED
NOT TO HURT MY CHILD.
ME FOR HIM.
Dio: SO BE IT THEN.
( squelch )
( blood pumps )
( baby crying )
( woman hisses )
SWEET LITTLE CHILD.
( growls )
( Dio chuckles )
AS PROMISED,
WE'VE NOT HARMED THE CHILD.
THAT'S SOMETHING YOU'VE
TAKEN CARE OF ON YOUR OWN.
THE IRONY IS LOST ON YOU.
A PITY.
( footsteps )
♪
Speedwagon: 'STREWTH, JONATHAN'S
DEMEANOR IS DIFFERENT,
AS IF THE SHUTTERS
WERE DRAWN ON HIS SOUL.
AND THE SAME FOR ME.
GOT NO TIME FOR TEARS,
ONLY ANGER.
THERE'LL BE
PLENTY OF TIME TO CRY
ONCE WE'VE DEALT WITH DIO.
OI, JONATHAN,
DIO WAS SWANNING ABOUT,
SAYING HE'D WIPE OUT THE TOWN
BY TOMORROW NIGHT.
ZOMBIES WILL MULTIPLY, LIKE RATS
BREEDING IN A REFUSE HEAP.
NO TELLING WHAT'S BEEN
GOING ON DOWN THERE.
IS WIND KNIGHTS LOT
ALIVE OR UNDEAD?
Poco: MY SISTER,
IS SHE ALL RIGHT?
JoJo: LET'S SEE.
♪
( Poco gasps )
Speedwagon: EH?
Poco: MR. ADAMS!
Adams: WELL, POCO,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AT THIS HOUR OF THE NIGHT
WANDERING THE MOORS?
Poco: PLEASE, TELL ME,
IS EVERYONE ALL RIGHT?
AND‐‐AND MY SISTER,
IS SHE SAFE?
Adams: YOU DARE TO ASK?
YOU MEAN TO SAY
YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW?
( all gasp )
‐ Adams: SHE'S BLOODY FURIOUS!
‐ ( cow moos )
WHEN YOU GET HOME,
SHE'S GONNA LOCK YOU IN THE BARN
AND TAN YOUR HIDE!
‐ JoJo: UH...
‐ Poco: UH...
JoJo: I GUESS
THAT MEANS SHE'S SAFE.
Speedwagon: HUH. THEN LET'S GO.
Poco: WELL,
THANK YOU, MR. ADAMS.
( Adams hisses )
A NICE YOUNG CHILD.
( cackles )
I HAVE A TASTE
FOR SOME FRESH, WARM BLOOD.
( laughs )
‐ ( Poco wails )
‐ ( Speedwagon gasps )
♪
( Adams roars )
JoJo: HE'S BEEN TURNED.
KEEP YOUR WITS ABOUT YOU.
Adams: YOU CAN'T ESCAPE ME
WITH YOUR HUMAN SPEED!
( JoJo yells )
( Adams gasps )
JoJo: THIS IS NO GOOD.
WE'RE TOO LATE AGAIN.
Man: THAT IS CORRECT.
♪
THE VILLAGE IS LOST.
THE ZOMBIES ARE EVERYWHERE.
Poco: OH, NO.
Speedwagon: NOT ANOTHER ONE.
Dire: I'M KNOWN AS DIRE.
JoJo: A KICK,
BUT WHY IS HE SO SLOW?
( Dire grunts )
( JoJo grunts )
( gasps )
Dire: TRY THIS!
THE THUNDER SPLIT ATTACK!
ARE YOU MAD, MAN?
A NORMAL MAN WOULD PULL BACK,
BUT INSTEAD
YOU WENT ON THE OFFENSIVE
AND ATTACKED ME
WITH A HEAD BUTT.
WAIT, PLEASE, JONATHAN JOESTAR,
‐ I AM HUMAN.
‐ ( JoJo gasps )
Dire: I APOLOGIZE.
YOU MUST FORGIVE ME.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE HOW WELL
ZEPPELI HAD TRAINED YOU.
JoJo: WHAT?
DID YOU SAY, "ZEPPELI"?
Dire: YOU HEARD CORRECTLY.
ZEPPELI IS
A DEAR OLD FRIEND OF MINE.
WE HAVE BEEN THROUGH
MANY TRIALS TOGETHER
OVER THE PAST 20 YEARS.
Man: THAT IS TRUE.
♪
HELLO. MY NAME IS STRAIZO.
PLEASE READ THIS.
JoJo: IT'S A LETTER.
IT WAS WRITTEN BY...
BARON ZEPPELI!
( Speedwagon and Poco gasp )
Straizo: WE'VE ONLY
JUST ARRIVED,
BUT HE SENT THAT SOME TIME AGO
REQUESTING OUR AID.
HE WROTE ABOUT THE STONE MASK,
WHERE IT COULD BE FOUND,
AND ESPECIALLY
ABOUT THE MAN WHO WEARS IT.
Poco: EH, HUH?
♪
JoJo: HMM?
‐ Dire: HMM?
‐ Straizo: MM.
Dire: OUR TRAINING MASTER,
TONPETTY.
( all gasp )
( Tonpetty exhales )
( gong reverberates )
GREETINGS TO YOU ALL.
JoJo: SO YOU'RE BARON ZEPPELI'S
TEACHER, MASTER TONPETTY.
Tonpetty: MM...
( JoJo gasps )
IN THE REGION I CALL HOME,
OUR CUSTOM IS
NOT TO SHAKE HANDS.
IN THIS WAY,
WE GREET EACH OTHER.
( all gasp )
Tonpetty: WHERE IS HE?
ZEPPELI SHOULD BE HERE NOW.
I SEE. ZEPPELI HAS
PASSED BEYOND THE VEIL.
( Dire gasps )
Tonpetty: EVEN IF
WE HAD ARRIVED EARLIER,
HIS FATE WOULD STILL
HAVE BEEN THE SAME.
HIS DEATH IS PROOF
THAT THE STRENGTH
THIS DIO WIELDS IS DEVASTATING.
HIS WICKEDNESS AND HIS POWER
ARE QUITE EXTRAORDINARY.
♪
( Dio chuckles )
HOW AMUSING.
I'VE PUT THIS TOWN IN MY THRALL
IN BUT A SINGLE NIGHT.
( chuckles )
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Creature: RUN, RUN, RUN!
Dire: FELL FOR IT,
DIDN'T YOU, FOOL?
Straizo: STRAIZO'S MY NAME.
NO MERCY.
JoJo: I WILL FEEL NO HINT
OF GUILT FOR YOUR DEATH.
Dio: COME, JOJO!