Smokey: I KNEW
THE MAN WAS CRAZY,
BUT NOT THAT CRAZY!
( glass tinkling )
♪
JoJo: STRAIZO!
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A CHOICE
ON HOW YOU WANT
TO MEET YOUR DEMISE.
WILL IT BE PLAIN OLD SUNLIGHT
OR HAMON?
OR I COULD
JUST SMASH IN YOUR BRAINS.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?!
( crowd yelling, screaming )
Woman: HE'S GOING
TO KILL US ALL!
JoJo: HUH?
Woman: SOMEONE CALL THE POLICE.
Smokey: JOJO, WHAT'D YOU‐‐
DID YOU LOSE YOUR MIND?
JUST LOOK AT WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
JoJo: HMM?
OHH.
HMM. YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'LL TAKE A SMALL FORTUNE
TO FIX EVERYTHING IN THIS PLACE.
Smokey: NOT THAT!
YOU JUST SHOT A PERSON!
JoJo: PERSON?
HAH! YOU MEAN STRAIZO?
THESE BULLETS I FIRED AT HIM
ALL HAVE STRANGE DENTS IN THEM.
THEY'VE BEEN COMPLETELY WARPED.
SMOKEY, GET OUT OF HERE NOW.
Smokey: EH?
JoJo: THAT THING I SHOT,
I CAN ONLY HOPE
THAT HE WAS A PERSON,
AND IF HE WAS,
I'LL HAPPILY GO TO JAIL
WITHOUT THINKING TWICE ABOUT IT.
‐ Smokey: BUT I DON'T‐‐
‐ ( women sobbing )
Smokey: WHAT ELSE WOULD HE BE?!
JoJo: CAN WE PLEASE
STOP THE CRYING?
I'M TRYING TO THINK HERE.
IF YOU DON'T CALM DOWN,
I MAY HAVE TO MAKE OUT WITH YOU.
EH?
♪
( crowd screaming )
( singing in Japanese )
( traffic honking )
♪
( bullet clatters )
( Straizo grunts )
( bullets clattering )
JoJo: JUST AS I FEARED,
STRAIZO IS INDEED A VAMPIRE.
Straizo: DIO'S FAILURE
WAS IN HIS INFATUATION
WITH HIS OWN POWER.
HE JUST COULDN'T RESIST
CONSTANTLY PUSHING
HIS OWN LIMITS.
HE STRETCHED HIMSELF THIN,
ALLOWING JONATHAN TO STRIKE HIM.
BUT I HAVE
A DIFFERENT PHILOSOPHY.
I FIGURE
I'LL HAVE PLENTY OF TIME
TO REFLECT ON THE EXTENT
OF MY POWERS
AFTER YOU'RE DESTROYED.
THERE WILL BE NO MERCY FOR YOU.
I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE APPROPRIATE
TO OPEN UP WITH THE TECHNIQUE
THAT DIO USED TO KILL JONATHAN.
‐ ( JoJo grunts )
‐ ( gun clicking )
( gasps )
Straizo: HEH. GUNS WILL FAIL.
HOWEVER, I CAN FIRE
HIGH‐PRESSURE ESSENCE
FROM MY EYES.
LOOK DEEPLY INTO MY SPACE‐RIPPER
STINGY EYES, JOSEPH.
‐ Smokey: JOJO!
‐ ( Straizo grunts )
THAT WAS A LITTLE TOO EASY.
NOW THE ONLY ONE LEFT
IS ERINA JOESTAR,
AND THAT SHOULD BE‐‐
JoJo: I KNOW
WHAT YOU'LL SAY NEXT.
Both: ABOUT AS EASY
AS TAKING CANDY FROM A BABY.
( Straizo gasps )
JoJo: HMM.
NEXT THING YOU'LL SAY IS,
"HOW COULD HE POSSIBLY BE ALIVE
WITH THAT HOLE IN HIS HEAD?"
AM I RIGHT?
Straizo: BUT‐‐BUT HOW COULD HE
POSSIBLY BE ALIVE WITH THAT HOLE
IN HIS HEAD? ( gasps )
JoJo: TOO MUCH TIME MEDITATING
OUT IN THE TIBETAN BOONIES
HAS DULLED YOUR SENSES.
THAT'S WHY I LIKE THE CITY.
IT KEEPS YOU SHARP.
YOU WOULDN'T BE
SO CONFUSED RIGHT NOW
IF YOU HAD JUST BEEN
A BIT MORE OBSERVANT.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S A HINT.
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO HAVE THE TIME, WOULD YOU?
I HEARD THE STORY ABOUT DIO
TAKING DOWN MY GRANDFATHER
BY FIRING SOME SORT OF BLAST
FROM HIS EYES.
Straizo: A MIRROR?!
JoJo: LOOK WHO
FINALLY NOTICED...
STRAIZ‐OAF!
I ALSO HEARD THAT YOU MAY BE
SEVERELY ALLERGIC TO HAMON,
JUST AS MUCH
AS YOU ARE TO SUNLIGHT!
( deep breath )
BATTER UP.
HERE COMES THE PITCH.
THAT'S OUTTA HERE!
♪
SO I HEAR THAT HAMON
DOES A PRETTY GOOD JOB
OF MELTING VAMPIRE FACES.
LET'S HAVE A LOOK HERE.
( gasps )
♪
( wails )
H‐HE'S UNHARMED.
IT'S AS THOUGH I NEVER EVEN
TOUCHED HIM AT ALL.
COULD IT BE POSSIBLE
THAT GRANNY WAS WRONG?
Straizo: NOT AT ALL.
YOUR GRANNY WAS NOT WRONG,
BECAUSE I CAN SEE THAT YOU WOULD
GROW INTO QUITE A WORTHY FOE
IF I DIDN'T HAVE
TO KILL YOU NOW.
HERE'S A SECRET BEFORE YOU DIE.
THERE IS AN INSECT
DEEP IN SOUTHEAST ASIA
CALLED THE SATIPOROJA BEETLE.
30,000 OF THEIR TINY STOMACHS
HAVE BEEN DRIED OUT
AND THEN WOVEN INTO THIS SCARF.
THEIR BODIES CONDUCT HAMON
FAR BETTER THAN THE HUMAN BODY,
THUS DISPERSING THE CHARGE.
IT'S SIMILAR
TO AN ELECTRICAL GROUND.
I HAVE INHERITED 4,000 YEARS
WORTH OF HISTORY AND RESEARCH
IN THE ART OF HAMON.
UNLIKE DIO,
I HAVE STUDIED THE CRAFT.
I AM A MASTER OF ITS STRENGTHS
AND FLAWS
IN ALL FORMS OF COMBAT.
JoJo: WOW,
THAT'S QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
NO, REALLY, IT IS.
BUT DID YOU THINK
I'D COMPLETELY RELY
ON A GIMMICK LIKE HAMON
ALL OF THE TIME?
Straizo: HMM?
JoJo: HMM.
I'M ALSO VERY FAST!
Straizo: WHAT THE‐‐
HOW DID YOU
PIN THAT GRENADE ON MY SCARF?
CHILD'S PLAY.
JoJo: SURE,
BUT I WAS STILL ABLE
TO PULL ONE OVER
ON YOU, WASN'T I?
AND YOU SHOULD TAKE A LOOK
AT THE GRENADE
YOU JUST KNOCKED AWAY.
( Straizo grunts )
YOU SON OF‐‐( screaming )
( crowd murmuring )
JoJo: WELL,
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
( rubble falling )
( gasps )
WH‐WHAT THE HELL IS HE?
( Smokey gasps )
JoJo: SMOKEY, I THOUGHT
I TOLD YOU TO RUN.
Smokey: IT'S TOO LATE
FOR THAT NOW.
PLEASE, GOD, I PROMISE I WON'T
EVER DO ANYTHING BAD AGAIN!
NO STEALING,
NO LYING, I SWEAR IT!
‐ PLEASE JUST SAVE ME!
‐ ( JoJo shudders )
♪
Smokey H‐HE'S A MONSTER.
YOU PROBABLY
KILL MONSTERS ALL THE TIME.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO,
RIGHT? JOJO?
JoJo: SURE. OF COURSE I DO.
Smokey: GREAT. I KNEW YOU WOULD.
JoJo: YEP.
I HAVE A SECRET WEAPON
FOR SITUATIONS SUCH AS THIS.
Smokey: A SECRET WEAPON?
REALLY? WHAT KIND OF WEAPON?
JoJo: WHY, ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
LOOK AT HIS LEGS, SMOKEY.
I BASICALLY BLEW THEM
TO SMITHEREENS,
AND THEY STILL
HAVEN'T FULLY HEALED YET.
THAT'S OUR TICKET THERE.
Smokey: WHAT DO HIS LEGS
HAVE TO DO WITH YOUR WEAPON?
JoJo: MY LEGS ARE
IN GREAT SHAPE.
Smokey: SO WHAT ARE
YOU GONNA DO, THEN?
JoJo: RUN AS FAST AS I CAN!
MAKE WAY! MOVE!
OUT OF THE WAY!
Smokey: THIS GUY IS INSANE!
♪
( thump )
JoJo: COME ON.
FOLLOW ME, STRAIZO.
Smokey: HEY, WAIT UP! JOJO!
( Straizo sighs )
I WILL MAKE HIM
PAY DEARLY FOR THAT.
EVEN THOUGH I'M IMMORTAL,
IT'LL TAKE SOME TIME
TO REGENERATE
AFTER WHAT HE DID TO ME.
( flash whooshes)
Reporter: THIS IS
A PERFECT SCOOP.
THE PAPERS WILL BE
FALLING ALL OVER THEMSELVES.
THIS IS MY CHANCE TO BREAK
INTO BIG‐TIME JOURNALISM.
Narrator: PRESSURE APPLIED
BY FINGERTIPS,
235 KILOGRAMS
PER CENTIMETER SQUARED.
( reporter gasps )
Narrator: LEAPING ABILITY,
CURRENTLY FOUR METERS,
22 CENTIMETERS.
Reporter:
IT'S BEHIND ME, ISN'T IT?
♪
( wind blowing )
( Smokey panting )
WE SHOULD BE SAFE
BY NOW, RIGHT?
JoJo: I'M AFRAID NOT, SMOKEY.
DO YOU HEAR THAT?
Smokey: DO I HEAR WHAT, JOJO?
ONLY THING I HEAR IS THE RIVER.
JoJo: NO, NOT THAT. LOOK UP!
♪
( reporter gasping )
( Smokey gasps )
HE FOLLOWED US HERE.
RUN, JOJO! RUN!
Straizo: I WOULD NOT DO THAT
IF I WERE YOU.
RUN AWAY,
AND I'LL KILL HER RIGHT HERE,
BUT COME UP AND MEET ME,
AND I WILL LET HER GO.
JoJo: WHAT SORT
OF THREAT IS THAT?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO THAT WOMAN IS, YOU MORON!
Smokey: JOJO, LET'S RUN.
Straizo: WHETHER YOU KNOW
THIS WOMAN OR NOT
IS INCONSEQUENTIAL.
IF YOU FLEE NOW,
I'LL KNOW JUST
WHAT SORT OF MAN YOU ARE.
RATHER THAN PURSUE YOU, I COULD
USE THIS TIME TO HEAL MYSELF,
FOR A TRUE COWARD WOULD
NOT SEEK REVENGE FOR SPEEDWAGON.
HOWEVER, IF YOU
WERE TO COME UP HERE
AFTER A GIRL
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW,
THEN I'LL SEE THAT YOU ARE
BOTH COURAGEOUS AND POWERFUL,
WHICH MEANS YOU'LL PRESENT
A REAL THREAT
AND CONTINUE TO PURSUE ME
INTO THE FUTURE,
AND I WOULD THEREFORE HAVE
TO ELIMINATE YOU HERE AND NOW.
I'LL KILL HER REGARDLESS.
FIGHT ME, OR RUN. DECIDE!
♪
( reporter gasps )
JoJo: BAH. GO AHEAD AND DO
WHAT YOU THINK
YOU NEED TO DO, STRAIZO.
I WOULDN'T FIGHT FOR THAT FLOOZY
EVEN IF I WAS MARRIED TO HER.
Straizo:
ARE YOU CERTAIN THAT THIS
IS THE TYPE OF GAME
YOU WISH TO PLAY?
IT WOULD BE SO EASY
TO TEAR THROUGH HER NECK
AND OPEN UP HER CHEST CAVITY
WITH JUST TWO FINGERS.
( JoJo laughs )
A TRUE MASTER OF TIBETAN HAMON
WOULD NEVER DO SUCH A THING.
SUCH GRATUITOUS CRUELTY
WOULD BE UNSEEMLY.
‐ ( crunch )
‐ ( reporter gasps )
( screams )
Smokey: THAT‐‐THAT WAS A TOOTH.
HE JUST RIPPED IT
RIGHT OUT OF HER MOUTH.
JoJo: JUST DESPICABLE.
THIS BASTARD HAS NO CONSCIENCE.
Straizo: CONSIDER THAT
YOUR LAST WARNING.
JoJo: YOU DEMONIC FREAK.
( growls )
RELEASE HER, STRAIZO!
YOU'LL PAY FOR THAT!
YOU'RE A VILE,
INHUMAN ABOMINATION!
Straizo: YOUR ACT
OF PLAYING IT CALM
BELIED THE FIRE
THAT WE SEE IN YOU NOW.
JoJo: LET'S SKIP
THE PRETTY SPEECHES.
NOW YOU'RE MINE!
( Straizo growls )
TAKE THIS!
JoJo: WHOA! NO!
FOOL ME ONCE, THEN SHAME ON ME.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY
FOR YOU, STRAIZO,
YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FOOL ME TWICE.
HAMON!
‐ ( Smokey gasps )
‐ ( Straizo gasps )
THAT'S IM‐‐
JoJo: NOW YOU'LL SAY,
"THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE."
Straizo: THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
( groans )
JoJo: I DEFLECTED YOUR SHOT
WITH A LITTLE HAMON SHOT GLASS.
I WAS PRETTY SURE YOU'D GO
FOR MY FOREHEAD AGAIN.
PREDICTABILITY CAN BE
QUITE THE FATAL FLAW.
( Straizo groans )
( JoJo breathes deeply )
( Straizo yells )
JoJo: GIVE MY BEST
TO SPEEDWAGON...
IN HELL!
( Straizo gags )
JoJo: GRANNY SHOULD BE ABLE
TO SLEEP WELL TONIGHT, FINALLY.
( Straizo grunting )
( wind blowing )
WHY WOULD YOU TRY
TO SAVE ME FROM FALLING?
AREN'T YOU FRIGHTENED THAT I
STILL POSSESS ENOUGH POWER IN ME
TO BLOW YOUR ARM CLEAN OFF?
JoJo: I'D LIKE
TO SEE YOU TRY THAT.
I'LL JUST PUMMEL YOU
INTO FERTILIZER
WITH MY REMAINING ARM.
I WANT SOME ANSWERS, STRAIZO.
TELL ME, WHY DID YOU
THROW SPEEDWAGON'S BODY
INTO THE RIVER?
SOMETHING HERE
JUST DOESN'T ADD UP.
Straizo: JOSEPH, YOUR
GRANDFATHER JONATHAN'S BLOOD
FLOWS THROUGH YOU.
FROM THE OUTSIDE,
YOU APPEAR TO BE OPPOSITES,
BUT YOU'RE BOTH
INSATIABLY CURIOUS.
AND NOW IT IS
MY PLEASURE TO WARN YOU
THAT YOUR NATURE
HAS TRAPPED YOU
IN A FATE
YOU CANNOT HOPE TO ESCAPE.
( JoJo gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
Straizo: SOON YOU SHALL LEARN
OF HIM, OF THE PILLAR MAN,
AND THEN YOU SHALL FINALLY
COME FACE TO FACE WITH HIM.
JoJo: OH, SHUT UP. I'M DONE
DECODING YOUR RUBBISH, STRAIZO.
Straizo: BUT I THREW THE BODIES
INTO THE RIVER BECAUSE OF HIM.
DON'T YOU SEE, FOOL?
THE PILLAR SUCKED DEEPLY
OF THE BLOOD
‐ ( blood flowing )
‐ FROM THOSE BODIES IN THE CAVE.
IT WAS LIKE A PLANT
RAVENOUSLY DRAWING IN NUTRIENTS.
IT WAS GHASTLY.
SO I DRAGGED
THE BODIES OUTSIDE.
BUT I HAVE NO DOUBTS NOW
THAT HE WILL SOON AWAKEN
FROM HIS 2,000‐YEAR SLUMBER.
( gasps )
NOT TO WORRY. IT IS FATED THAT
YOU SHALL MEET HIM VERY SOON,
AND WHEN THAT TIME COMES,
YOU SHALL LEARN HIS IDENTITY
AND THE TRUE MEANING
OF EVOLUTION.
YOUR DESTINY
HAS ALREADY BEEN WRITTEN.
( JoJo gasps )
IS THAT HAMON?
SO THAT MEANS...
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
CREATING HAMON
INSIDE YOUR OWN BODY.
Straizo: THERE IS
NOTHING I REGRET, JOSEPH.
ALL THIS TIME,
I PLANNED ON ENTERING HELL
WHILE STILL VIBRANT
AND FILLED WITH ENERGY,
NOT AS SOME WITHERED,
DESICCATED CORPSE.
I CANNOT TELL YOU THE ECSTASY
THAT I HAVE FELT
IN BEING YOUNG AGAIN.
JoJo: STRAIZO, WAIT! NOT YET!
I NEED TO KNOW MORE!
Straizo: FAREWELL TO YOU, JOJO.
♪
( JoJo shuddering )
Smokey: JOJO.
( JoJo screaming )
Narrator: 1938.
THE SECOND WORLD WAR RAGES,
THREATENING TO ENGULF
MORE NATIONS AROUND THE GLOBE
WITH EACH PASSING DAY.
AS THE GERMAN ARMY GROWS,
IT SEEKS TO CONQUER THE WORLD
WITH TECHNOLOGY
AND WEAPONS THAT STAND
AT THE VERY CUTTING EDGE
OF SCIENCE.
HOWEVER, THEY ALSO RESEARCH
ASTROLOGY, SORCERY,
ALCHEMY, AND PSYCHIC POWERS.
THEY SEEK TO GAIN ADVANTAGES
THROUGH EVERY MANNER IMAGINABLE
IN THEIR QUEST
FOR GLOBAL DOMINATION.
AND IT WAS
THROUGH THIS TENACITY
THAT ONE OF THEIR
SPY NETWORKS IN MEXICO
CAUGHT WIND
OF STRAIZO'S ACTIONS.
♪
( woman gasping )
I'M‐‐I'M SO TERRIBLY SORRY,
MAJOR VON STROHEIM.
MY HAND, IT JUST SLIPPED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
♪
( Von Stroheim sighs )
LICK IT.
( woman gasps )
Von Stroheim:
YOU DREW BLOOD FROM ME, NO?
DON'T MAKE ME ORDER YOU
TO LICK MY WOUND CLEAN.
Woman: YES, SIR.
Von Stroheim: GENTLY NOW.
I KNOW YOU WOULDN'T WANT
TO HURT ME AGAIN.
GOOD. SLOWLY NOW. SLOWLY.
MMM. I THINK THE PAIN
IS GOING AWAY.
‐ NOW...
‐ ( woman gasping )
Von Stroheim:
BE CAREFUL NOW. CAREFUL NOW.
DON'T CUT YOUR TONGUE.
( laughs )
Soldier: PARDON MY INTERRUPTION,
MAJOR VON STROHEIM.
Von Stroheim: HMM?
( woman gasps )
Soldier: THE OLD MAN FOUND
ON THE BANK OF THE RIO DADA,
HE IS NOW AWAKE,
MAJOR VON STROHEIM.
SHALL WE INTERROGATE, SIR?
( Speedwagon groans )
JoJo: ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, MISS?
CAN YOU TELL ME YOUR NAME?
ALLOW ME TO ESCORT YOU HOME.
EH?
WHY IN THE HELL
DID YOU DO THAT?!
Reporter: YOU'VE GOT SOME NERVE
CALLING ME A FLOOZY,
YOU BIG BRUTE!
JUST WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE, ANYWAY, HUH?
JoJo: WHAT? I NEVER SAID THAT.
Smokey: NO, YOU DID.
YOU SAID THAT YOU WOULD NEVER
FIGHT FOR A FLOOZY LIKE HER.
JoJo: REALLY?
WOW, I DIDN'T MEAN IT.
I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT THAT.
IT JUST HAPPENED KINDA‐‐
AGH!
Reporter: YEAH,
I'M SURE IT "JUST HAPPENS"
EVERY TIME
YOU TALK ABOUT A WOMAN.
( JoJo groans )
YOUR MOUTH OKAY?
( reporter screams )
( JoJo sighs )
LOOKS LIKE THE ADRENALINE
FROM HER FEAR JUST WORE OFF.
NOW IT'S TIME TO FIND OUT
ABOUT THIS PILLAR MAN
STRAIZO WAS TALKING ABOUT.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE MEXICO.
( fly buzzing )
( Von Stroheim groans,
coughing )
HOW ARE YOU FEELING‐‐
( coughs ) SPEEDWAGON?
THERE IS A SAYING IN EUROPE
THAT COMES TO MIND.
"THE VILLAGE IN WHICH
THE ELDERLY KILL EACH OTHER
IS NOT LONG FOR THIS WORLD."
YOU HAVE A SECRET,
A SECRET THAT IS VERY DANGEROUS
AND COULD KILL US ALL.
I WANT ANSWERS NOW!
( Speedwagon gasps )
Von Stroheim:
THERE APPEARS TO BE A MAN
TRAPPED INSIDE THIS PILLAR.
WE EXTRACTED IT FROM
THE LOCATION WE GOT FROM YOU.
( Speedwagon groans )
WHY, GOD? WHY DO THIS TO ME?
WHY COULDN'T YOU JUST
HAVE LET ME DIE BACK THERE?
WHY DID YOU MAKE ME LIVE?!
Von Stroheim: IT WASN'T GOD.
AT LEAST, NOT YOUR GOD.
I WAS THE ONE WHO MADE YOU LIVE,
BUT I CAN CHANGE THAT.
THE WEHRMACHT WOULD LIKE
SOME INFORMATION FROM YOU
BEFORE ANYTHING DRASTIC HAPPENS.
( Speedwagon gasps )
Von Stroheim:
YOU ARE STUBBORN, OLD MAN.
I'M SMART ENOUGH TO KNOW
THAT TORTURE ALONE
WOULD NOT GIVE US
WHAT WE WANT OUT OF YOU.
I ALSO KNOW
THAT YOU WERE PENNILESS
WHEN YOU FIRST GOT TO TEXAS.
YOU WERE NEARLY DEAD
IN THE DESERT
WHEN YOU FOUND THE OIL FIELDS
THAT WOULD SOON CAUSE
A MASSIVE OVERHAUL
OF THE WORLD'S ECONOMY.
GET READY!
GERMAN MEDICINE IS
THE GREATEST THING IN THE WORLD,
DON'T YOU THINK?!
WE CAN DO ANYTHING!
Speedwagon: A TRUTH SERUM?
FOR WHAT? WHAT MORE COULD
YOU POSSIBLY WANT FROM ME?
Von Stroheim: EVERYTHING!
I WANT TO KNOW IT ALL.
GIVE ME A HISTORY LESSON.
TELL ME ABOUT STRAIZO
UND ABOUT THIS JOESTAR.
TELL US SO THAT WE CAN
FINALLY AWAKEN THE PILLAR MAN.
Speedwagon: NO. NO, YOU CAN'T.
YOU DON'T KNOW THE FORCES
YOU'RE PLAYING WITH.
( Von Stroheim gargling )
Speedwagon: HE'S POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO DESTROY US ALL.
Von Stroheim:
MAKE THE NECESSARY PREPARATIONS
FOR THE BLOOD FEEDING
EXPERIMENT,
UND DON'T SCREW ANYTHING UP.
Prisoner: HELP US! LET US OUT!
Prisoner #2:
I'LL DO ANYTHING! PLEASE!
‐ Von Stroheim: HMM.
‐ ( pleading quiets )
I HAVE A PROPOSAL FOR YOU.
GO AHEAD UND CHOOSE SOMEONE
FROM AMONG YOURSELVES.
( prisoners murmuring )
Von Stroheim: WE NEED BLOOD
FOR A VERY IMPORTANT,
HISTORIC EXPERIMENT.
ONCE YOU HAVE ALL AGREED
ON WHO WILL BE THE ONE
TO SACRIFICE HIS LIFE,
WE WILL GRANT THE REST OF YOU
YOUR FREEDOM IMMEDIATELY.
( prisoners murmuring )
‐ Boy: ME. I VOLUNTEER FOR IT.
‐ Von Stroheim: EH?
Boy: IF I DO YOUR EXPERIMENT,
YOU PROMISE THAT YOU'LL
LET EVERYONE ELSE GO, RIGHT?
Von Stroheim:
YOU ARE QUITE BRAVE.
COURAGE LIKE YOURS IS A THING
THAT MUST BE CULTIVATED
LIKE A LUSH GARDEN.
HERE, WE WILL ALLOW
ONLY THE MOST FIT TO LIVE.
SET THE BOY ASIDE,
UND EXECUTE EVERYONE ELSE.
( prisoners gasp, wail )
♪
Von Stroheim:
LET THE EXPERIMENT BEGIN!
‐ ( heart beating )
‐ ( blood flowing )
♪
♪ I'LL BE THE ROUNDABOUT
♪ THE WORDS
WILL MAKE YOU OUT AND OUT ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ THE MUSIC DANCE AND SING
♪ THEY MAKE THE CHILDREN
REALLY RING ♪
♪ I SPEND THE DAY YOUR WAY
♪ CALL IT MORNING
DRIVING THROUGH THE SOUND ♪
♪ AND IN AND OUT THE VALLEY
♪ IN AND AROUND THE LAKE
♪ MOUNTAINS COME
OUT OF THE SKY ♪
♪ AND THEY STAND THERE
♪ ONE MILE OVER,
WE'LL BE THERE ♪
♪ AND WE'LL SEE YOU
♪ 10 TRUE SUMMERS, WE'LL BE
THERE AND LAUGHING, TOO ♪
♪ 24 BEFORE, MY LOVE,
YOU'LL SEE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WITH YOU
♪
Speedwagon: YOU'VE NO IDEA
WHAT HE'S CAPABLE OF!
JoJo: ALL I'VE GOT
UNDER MY SKIRT
‐ IS MORE TEQUILA, BIG BOY.
‐ Pillar Man: WHICH ONE OF YOU
WAS FOOL ENOUGH
TO DISTURB MY SLUMBER?
Von Stroheim:
HE'S SQUEEZING HIMSELF
INTO THE VENTILATION DUCTS!