Mister Maou.
I have to go.
Chiho.
It's time for me
to return to Ente Isla.
Oh, please.
No!
Why can't you
just stay here?
With me?
I'm sorry, but I cannot
linger in this world any longer.
I must go.
Fine, then I'll go
with you to Ente Isla.
Please take me with you!
[MAOU] That is the
one thing I cannot do.
By rights, you and I
live in different worlds.
We never should have even met.
Chi.
Forgive me.
Mister Maou.
Mister Maou!
And that was everything
that happened in my nightmare.
The end.
Well, interesting.
So what happened next?
Like after I said
I was going back home.
Pardon?
What happened next?
You uh-- You kinda--
[MAOU] Well, whatever.
I can't go now anyway.
I don't have
enough magic left.
Man, yesterday
was so exhausting.
Having to restore
all those broken buildings
after a fight was rough.
Not to mention opening
a Gate to get rid of Sariel.
I used up every
bit of magic I had.
Oh.
Hey Chi, have you
seen Maa around?
[MAOU] Right here!
Kawa-cchi told
me something.
Is it true last night you
grabbed a mop, ran out of
the restaurant like a crazy
person, and never came back?
[MAOU] Yeah, about that.
There were extenuating
circumstances.
Why are you
making excuses?
[SUZUNO] The truth is Good
Sadao saved us last night.
Evening.
[URUSHIHARA] Hm.
Looks like Crestia Bel's
visiting MiggyR's right now.
[ASHIYA] Your voyeurism
is in very poor taste,
even if it is
for surveillance.
Wait!
You did not
stop at Emilia?
You planted a tracker
on Crestia Bel, too?
How much did
that cost us?
Dude, how about you
stop touching me
with your soapy hands.
And who might you be?
[SUZUNO] My name
is Suzuno Kamazuki.
Good Chiho and I were on
our way home last night when
a deviant attacked us out of
the blue, and the good Sadao
rushed to our location
to provide assistance.
Yeah! He's a hero!
I honestly don't know
what would have happened if
he hadn't been here
to rescue us!
You fought off a
deviant with a mop?
[MAOU] Yeah, he was a
bit of a tough customer.
Well, I suppose that
does count as extenuating.
[knock]
[KAWA-CCHI] Excuse
me, Miss Kisaki,
some dude just fell
out of the walk-in!
[MAOU] Sariel.
[CHIHO] But I thought you
threw him into the Gate.
[SUZUNO] Good Sadao, perhaps
that garland you used responded
to the Devil's magic by opening
the other end of the Gate
inside the restaurant and
dropped Sariel off here.
Oh good; he's alive.
Are you okay, sir?
Not dead or anything?
Beautiful.
How strange is fortune!
I had to travel to another world
to meet the goddess of beauty.
O goddess, so desperate
am I for thy forbidden love
that I may fall all
the way from Heaven!
Okay, who is
this freakshow?
Actually, he
manages the SFC.
Truth!
My beloved he speaks truth!
We are indeed from two
irreconcilable organizations.
You from MgRonald's,
I from Sentucky.
We are the
Romeo and Juliet
of the fast food industry.
Looks like that fall
gave you some brain damage.
And I think it might be too late
for an ambulance to help.
[SARUE] O!
Such kind words from such
a beautiful mouth speaking
of concern for my health!
Sadly, no miracle of medicine
can mend a lovesick heart;
for me, my goddess
the only cure is your love!
[KISAKI] All right then,
would you rather
I call the police, you perv?
[SARUE] This is what
tempts angels to fall!
O, please don't
stop my love.
What sweet, sweet agony!
[EMI] Again,
my name is Miss Yusa.
Thank you so much for
allowing me to assist you.
Goodbye.
What's going on?
What is this?
[evil laugh]
[MAOU] I rule over
this city at last!
And now, for my
next conquest--Greenland!
[maniacal laugh]
Stupid nightmares.
[EMI] Well, I doubt MgRonald's
will realistically be
the new Devil's Castle,
but that still doesn't mean
I can let my guard down.
[RIKA] So, uh, Emi, you
seem kinda fired up today.
Oh, you think so?
You got any plans later;
I was thinking we could
grab dinner if you want?
[EMI] I would love to,
but I can't tonight.
[RIKA] Don't tell me you're
gonna go check on Maou again.
[EMI] Not check on so
much as keep tabs on.
Seriously?
Don't you think it's
past time you two let go
of all that negativity
and bad blood?
[EMI] Not at all.
Uh.
It's complicated,
but it's not like a big deal.
[EMI] My village gone.
My father killed.
Why would I ever
forgive that?
Could I?
No.
It doesn't matter; I'm a hero,
and he's the Devil.
Who knows when he'll be my enemy
again, just like in my dream.
[EMI] Knock-knock!
What is going
on here?
[CHIHO] Oh hi,
Miss Yusa!
Hey!
Miss Suzuno,
what are you doing?
Well, I made an attempt
to cook French food earlier,
so he's eating Udon Confit
with Sauce Americaine.
[CHIHO] Unbelievable!
I already said I'd be making
dinner for him today!
And Mister Maou,
you're just sitting there
going along with this?
[MAOU] What?
I uh-- What?
Cut it out; you're
supposed to be his enemy,
aren't you?
Come on!
And you're hand feeding
him like I wanted to!
Careful, Chiho,
your real feelings
are starting to show.
[CHIHO] You keep your
fat mouth out of this.
Fine.
Mister Maou,
whose dinner
are you gonna eat--
mine or your enemy's?
[MAOU] Um.
Budget-wise, it'd help if you
both took turns bringing dinner
every day but you
know, it's whatever.
[SUZUNO] Oh,
that's not a problem.
[CHIHO] No!
Not a problem at all!
This is evil incarnate?
A word, Sire.
Yo, Ashiya!
Finally; where've
you been?
I have grave business
to discuss.
[MAOU] What's with
the formality?
Formality is
appropriate when asking
for time off.
[EMERALDA] What?
You think Alciel
is visiting his home?
I don't know about that;
I've not heard about him
returning to Ente Isla.
I know it's unexpected,
but Alciel himself said
he wanted time off
for something.
[EMERALDA] Well, there are lots
of different types of vacations.
Maybe he's just sick of being
cramped inside that itty bitty
Devil's Castle all day.
Yeah, I'd agree,
but that wasn't the vibe
I was getting at all.
You want time off?
But what for?
Alas, I can't
speak of it here.
I see.
Sorry, would you guys
mind excusing us for the day.
Ashiya needs to talk
to me about something.
--[SUZUNO] All right.
--[CHIHO] All right.
I see what you
mean; that seems
more than a little
suspicious to me, too.
[CHIHO] Miss Emeralda didn't
know what was going on, either?
[EMI] No, but just to be safe,
I'm having her sniff around
for anything happening in
Ente Isla that seems like it
might be out of the ordinary.
[thunder]
Well, we won't
get far in this.
[CHIHO] Do you think maybe--
Do you think Mister Maou might
go back to Ente Isla now?
I'm scared that what if
my dream is coming true?
How come? What did
you dream about?
Oh. Nothing really.
You know that's really
weird; I had a kind of
ominous dream, myself.
What? Are you serious?
Don't you worry about it.
I promise, Chiho, while
I'm around I'll never let
anything sad happen to you.
It's cool.
[EMI] So many boxes.
Did they go shopping?
No, there's no way they
have that kind of money.
What are those boys up to?
I got a package
from Emeralda,
so anything's possible.
Could that be stuff
from the demon realm?
[EMERALDA] There really
isn't anything going on.
I had Albert
look into it for us,
and he didn't hear even
the slightest buzz.
The only strange thing
is that nothing strange
is being reported.
Oh, but there is one major
problem that's stressing me out!
What is it?
I'm starting
to gain weight,
and I'm completely devastated.
What?
How is that at all relevant?
[RIKA] Huh?
Emi, is that you?
What is going on over there?
Nothin', just
thinking out loud!
[KISAKI] Unbelievable.
What is that dwarf
manager thinking?
[knock]
[MAOU] Miss Kisaki.
I'm uh-- sorry for the short
notice, but is there any way
I can get a little time off?
[KISAKI] What?
That's unexpected.
Yeah.
I had something major come up,
and I can't get out of it.
Got it. Yeah.
I can work around that;
so whatever you need.
Great, thank
you, Ma'am.
[KISAKI] Just let me know what
days, and I'll take care of it.
[MAOU] Alright!
[MAOU] Aw.
It's raining again?
Mister Maou,
are you gonna go home
to Ente Isla after all?
That's why you're
taking off work, right?
Okay, but please don't tell me
you're never coming back!
Chi.
I already said I don't
have enough magic.
So then, why did
you get time off?
Because.
Sorry.
I can't tell you why.
[CHIHO] Mister Maou.
[CHIHO] Are you sure
we should be doing this?
Don't you think it would
be better to give him
the benefit of the doubt?
Who would it be
better for, though?
I wish I could, but
with all those boxes,
he's definitely
up to something.
Our only choice is
to find out the truth.
Yeah, but--
Sh!
Come on,
let's tail him.
[CHIHO] A construction site?
[EMI] Could he be starting to
build a new Devil's Castle here?
[CHIHO] He couldn't
afford to do that.
It looks like
he's just working.
But why?
[MAOU] Girls, I can see you!
We just needed to get our
hands on some money fast
so we could pay off a
couple tracking devices.
Tracking devices?
Urushihara bought 'em
online and then decided
to hide one tracker in your
purse and the other one
in Suzuno's sandals.
How dare he?
[MAOU] Stop!
This is not the place to
whip out your sacred sword!
And remember, they did help
when Sariel kidnapped you,
so don't be so mad!
I'll kill him!
[MAOU] Anyway, they're
gonna debit our account
for those next week.
And right now,
we're completely broke.
I won't get my MgR's check
until after they charge me.
So then, Ashiya decided he
wanted to get one of those
temp jobs that would
pay him by the day.
Oh, so that's why
he asked for time off?
Of course.
I took time off my job to
temp with him so I could
help him out in case
things got dicey.
But it looks like
the agency sent Ashiya
to work somewhere else.
If that's all it was,
why'd you feel the need
to hide it from Chiho?
Well, you see because--
I was worried if I
told her about it,
she'd wind up feeling
responsible since the trackers
we're working to pay for are
what helped me rescue her.
So--
I'm sorry, Chi.
Don't worry about it.
I'm just glad you're
not planning to go back
to Ente Isla or anything.
Okay, so then what's the
deal with the truckload of boxes
you had delivered to your house?
[MAOU] What?
What boxes?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
[URUSHIHARA] What boxes?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Gimme a break, guys,
all this stuff has been here
since before I moved in.
We both know that's
not the truth, you liar.
Now get out of my way!
[MAOU] Feather beds?
[CHIHO] Fire extinguishers?
[EMI] Water purifiers?
[CHIHO] And there're
so many of them!
[MAOU] Urushihara,
what is all of this?
Hah.
You know, it's a
funny story actually.
I did some online research,
and apparently what happened
is called a "buy-up-scam."
This sounds expensive.
[EMI] Yeah, see, someone
knocks on your door and offers
to buy your stuff.
But instead, they wind up
pressuring you into buying
a bunch of their crap.
Well, on a
positive note,
he did buy the external
hard drive from me.
Then, he kinda made
me buy all that.
[MAOU] How much?
How much did it cost?
A lot.
Like what you
make in a month.
[URUSHIHARA squeals]
[SUZUNO] Unfortunately,
it seems you fell victim to a
very underhanded salesperson.
He fell victim?
More like nose-dived.
I can't help it.
I'm socially
awkward!
[SUZUNO] Maou, torturing
the poor idiot at this point
won't accomplish anything.
This is the
company, isn't it?
[CHIHO] Deluxe Life
International Holdings?
What?
That doesn't even
sound like a real name.
Why not give
them a call?
[CUSTOMER SERVICE] Hello;
thank you for calling
Deluxe Life
International Holdings.
How may I assist
you this afternoon?
Yeah, the other day
a door-to-door salesman
sold us feather beds,
fire extinguishers,
and water purifiers.
We're not gonna use those,
so we'd like to
return them, please.
[CUSTOMER SERVICE]
I'm terribly sorry, sir,
but we run tests on the water
purifiers when we install them
to make sure they work.
Since they're essentially
used items we cannot
accept them as returns.
Well, we haven't used the
twenty years' worth of filters
that came with them,
so you can take those back.
[CUSTOMER SERVICE]
Unfortunately,
they do come as a set
with the purifiers.
We're unable to
refund just the filters.
As for the fire extinguishers,
they've already been installed
as well, which means,
under the Fire Service Act's
safety guidelines, it's illegal
for us to take them back,
even though they may be unused.
[MAOU] What about
the feather beds, then?
[CUSTOMER SERVICE] We accept
returns for those,
as long as they're
completely unused also.
That was a set
of seven, correct?
[MAOU] No, not correct,
it's a set of five.
[CUSTOMER SERVICE] I'm afraid
our company only sells sets
of seven.
We can't accept any sets
that are short parts,
so I'm sorry, but--
[MAOU] Just forget it!
Lemme guess, they have
no intention of taking
anything back, right?
So, what are
you gonna do?
Go there in person?
Go there in person!
[MAOU] This is it.
[doorbell]
[CUSTOMER SERVICE] Coming!
Uh?!
Whoa, Ashiya?
Your Majesty?
And Emilia, too?
What brings you here?
This is seriously
where the temp agency
sent you to work?
Well, now I know why that
voice seemed so familiar.
[EMI] Let's get to the point;
what's your deal?
I don't have a "deal;"
I'm just following the procedure
for handling unreasonable
demands for returns.
Wait, hold on a second!
Why on Earth did he
buy seven feather beds?
[MAOU] I told you,
he was swindled!
And it wasn't seven,
it was five.
[ASHIYA] Oh dear, that sounds
like a scam if you ask me!
Because it is a scam,
which is what I've
been trying to say!
Then what you're really
trying to say is I've been sent
to this company to practice
fraudulent business dealings,
and unwittingly acted as an
agent of evil in the process!
[EMI] Are you or are you not a
big-time demon generalissimo?
Now that I am aware of
the truth, I cannot remain here
and dishonor myself with
this association any longer.
[MAN] Why are we yelling?
Sir, you're here.
Do we have a problem?
[MAOU] Yeah.
You're the jerk in charge, huh?
Now, we don't
have to be rude.
Why don't we talk this
over calmly instead.
I'm sure this was explained over
the phone, sir, but you can find
the same info on the provisions
of the signed contract.
What do you
mean provisions?
I've never seen
this contract.
[MAN] Oh?
Well, you received a copy.
I really must ask you
to follow the rules.
"Rules" my
left foot!
This whole thing
is a scam!
All participants fully
consented to the arrangement.
[MAOU] Consented?
Consented?
Who'd be dumb enough
to buy seven feather beds
for one tiny apartment?
[MAN] Someone
who lives with you.
[MAOU] You bastard!
You're being smug because
you think we can't
do anything about this!
I didn't sell any
defective merchandise,
so you've got no reason
or right to complain.
Again, we have a legally
binding contract.
Though I don't mind
settling this outside.
[MAOU] We lost.
[ASHIYA] Perhaps the best
course of action would be
to consult the police.
[EMI] Nah, you can't rely on
cops to take care of this.
Sure, he's crooked, but
there's still a contract.
And we have no proof
it was a scam.
[ASHIYA] So, basically
there is nothing to be done.
[MAOU] Damn it!
How are we ever gonna get
all the money together
to pay for that crap?
[ASHIYA] My apologies, Sire.
I do believe I am partly
to blame; after all,
I've been remiss in my
duties as his guardian.
His guardian?
Hold up a sec you guys,
how old is Urushihara, again?
And not his Ente Isla age;
I mean here in this world.
[MAOU] Oh.
Let's see.
I'm pretty sure
I made him eighteen
on all the official records.
In that case,
I think I know a trick that
should help you demons out.
Help us?
You mean as in not having to
fork over money we don't have?
Tell us this trick
of yours, wench!
It's called "Cooling-Off."
[LAWYER] A guardian's consent
is required for any contract
signed by a person
under the age of twenty.
That is unless the
contract is for less than
their allowance.
Mister Maou, the good news is
you're Mister Urushihara's
recognized guardian.
So the "cooling-off"
rule applies
in this circumstance.
[ASHIYA] Honestly!
He completely bamboozled us!
True dat; I still can't
believe we met a human
who could out-bedeviled
the Devil.
And we were saved
by the Hero Emilia;
who would have thought?
Well, she's used to
return-happy customers.
Maybe one day we can get
her over on our side.
Surely you jest, Sire.
And uh-- I'm ready
to order when you are.
Cool, I'm gonna have
what you're having.
[BOTH]
Excuse us!
Two Cat's Dooms please!
[EMI] Are you
dense or something?
Hi, Emi.
To think the Devil
himself is waiting out
in the pouring rain
with no umbrella.
Shut up.
Take this.
Hmm?
I threw out the umbrella
I borrowed from you before,
so I'm replacing it
with a new one.
Don't be such an ingrate.
Take the thing already.
Just take it!
Yeah. Fine.
So uh-- Thanks, I guess.
[EMI] You are very welcome.