[MAOU in Ente Islan]
[OLBA in Ente Islan]
[EMILIA in Ente Islan]
I saw you cast a spell.
Tell me, Satan, why
would the King of Darkness
be working part-time
at a MgRonalds?
The Hero, Emilia?
Yeah, forget about me,
what are you doing here?
[EMILIA] I leapt through
the Gate, just like you.
[EMILIA] This moment
shall be your last.
[MAOU] Emilia,
wait! I can explain!
No. I don't want to hear
what you have to say!
Prepare to die, Devil!
Let's chat, okay?
No, let's don't.
I'm not here to talk it out;
I'm here to kill you.
Cool. It's just your knife.
Isn't it from that crappy
hundred-yen store downtown?
What? I--
What's your stupid point?
[MAOU] Where's
your Sacred Sword?
It-- You know what, that's
not really any of your business.
[MAOU] Have you by chance
lost your Celestial Force?
Or maybe you just can't
afford to waste it?
[EMILIA] Well, you're in
the same boat, aren't you?
The magic I'm sensing
from you right now
is practically nothing compared
to what it was in Ente Isla.
Duh. Obviously;
I'm on a bike.
[EMILIA] Sword or no sword,
a Devil without magic
working fast-food is not an
adversary I need to worry about!
En garde!
My poor, poor ingredients.
[ASHIYA] His Majesty
sure is late.
Now, tell me why you
two were fighting
in the middle of the street.
[EMILIA] Because
I must destroy him.
"Destroy him"? Look, lady.
I don't know what
your boyfriend did,
and it doesn't really matter.
No knife fighting.
You can't do that.
Did you say
boyfriend?
Bet he thinks
we're dating
and I cheated
or dumped you.
I am not in a romantic
relationship with this freak!
I getcha.
If you've decided you would like
to end things with him, though,
you need to be
more mature about it.
I'm cutting you some
slack today, so get lost.
Huh?
But this will
be the last time.
And by the way,
I know where you live.
I'm confident tonight will
be the last good night's
sleep you'll ever have.
Not nice.
Doesn't really sound like the
kinda thing a hero should say.
I didn't ask for the opinion
of a part-time Devil!
Yeah, okay, whatever.
Gimme back my umbrella,
discount store hero.
You told me I could
throw it away, remember?
I took it carefully apart
and put it in the trash.
[MAOU] Rude!
I'm a hero--I can't just
leave the Devil's umbrella
lying around for an
innocent to discover.
Ugh. You are such a pain.
That's right.
Starting tomorrow you
should watch your back. Hmph!
[MAOU] She sure doesn't
seem all that heroic to me.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 2A]
Yes, Sir. We can do that.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 2B]
I do apologize, Ma'am.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 2C] So which
calling plan sounds best?
Right. Again,
my name is Miss Yusa.
And thank you so much for
allowing me to assist you.
Jeez!
I've had like five
million complaints today.
Least try crackin' open a
manual for once, am I right?
Oh. Hey, so--
you wanna grab lunch
at that curry place
that just opened?
[EMILIA] Eh, don't you think
it'll still be too crowded?
[RIKA] I guess we could
just go the Miggy R's route
if you're worried about time.
No! Anything
but that. Sorry.
[RIKA] Gross. Another one.
[EMILIA] Here we go.
Back to it.
[BOTH] Thank you for calling
the Docodemo Customer
Service Center!
How may I help you, today?
[MALE REPORTER 2A] It's time
for "Crash That Dinner!"
All right folks,
this is the next house
that's about to get crashed!
Wow, I've definitely
caught the scent
of something enticing
all of a sudden!
[MALE REPORTER 2A]
Why, this looks sumptuous!
Is that a steak I see?
Are we celebrating
something this evening?
Aha! Now, I see
why it smells so good!
Focus on this, camera guy!
You're using high-quality
meat, aren't you, Ma'am?
Could this be one of the most
expensive cuts out there?
How is what
I'm doing right now
any different than what
that buffoon is up to?
Wish we had a little
more protein this time.
You eat hamburgers on an
almost daily basis, Sire;
you get plenty.
[doorbell]
Dinner crasher guy?
I'm gonna say no.
Salesperson?
[ASHIYA] I doubt we live
in the kind of neighborhood
where people feel comfortable
going door to door
in an attempt to
sell anything legal.
[ASHIYA] Hello. To whom
do we owe the pleasure?
[EMILIA] That's an
unexpectedly courteous greeting
coming from a demon.
Especially you, General Alciel.
I assume you
also remember me.
Emilia the Hero.
[gasps]
Emilia the Hero?
[EMILIA] Yes! Now, open
this door immediately!
Accept your punishment
with a little dignity! Hey!
It's the Hero, Sire!
The Hero is here
and she hath found us!
Yeah. I kinda
know already.
You knew she was here
and didn't say anything?
Mmm... I probably
should have mentioned it
to you earlier.
I ran into her yesterday;
she mighta tried to kill me.
[EMILIA] Hurry up!
[sighs] The cops thought
we were dating
and having a "lovers quarrel."
[EMILIA] Yeah and it was the
most mortifying thing ever!
Me, dating the ruler of demons?
[knocking]
And now she's here.
Might I ask why you didn't feel
the need to tell me this, Sire?
[MAOU] Well, I figured she
didn't do any real damage.
Other than completely
stressing me out,
she doesn't have any powers
left to use against me.
So, she's like us.
And most likely
doesn't have the ability
to replenish her powers
in this world either.
Which means the Hero has
no more control
of the Gate than we.
[MAOU] Aw, let her in.
[EMILIA sobbing]
[door opening]
[EMILIA] This place is a dump.
It's shabby, it's tiny,
and it's got paper-thin walls.
[MAOU] Okay, now
you're just being mean.
[sniffles]
[ASHIYA] The Devil's
Castle prioritizes
functionality over comfort.
Oh, really? This is what
you call functional?
Quite the royal feast
you got there.
Hey, Ashiya is
an amazing cook!
He whips up meals out
of practically nothing;
it's like magic.
I am truly honored by
your kind praise, Sire.
Many thanks.
[MAOU] Word.
Are you both idiots?
The Prince of Lies
is really dining
on jelly and cucumbers?
What's your problem?
We can't help being poor.
[EMILIA] For real?
Did I travel all the way
from another world just
to kill this disaster?
It's pathetic!
I mean, even I've
found a better way
to live than this,
and I live all by myself!
[MAOU]
Your comrades aren't here?
No! And shut up!
I'm all alone here.
One of the high priests
was supposed to come, too.
Our plan was to go back home
as soon as we destroyed
you in this world.
But then Olba was--He
was too slow.
[In Ente Islan]
[OLBA in Ente Islan]
[EMILIA in Ente Islan]
It turned out I was the
only one to make it through.
[MAOU] That sucks.
Thanks, but the last thing
I need is a demon's pity.
'Tis rather amusing;
you're like a search party that
requires its own search party.
Well, now that that's settled,
you should find
yourself a way home.
You know where we live,
but it's not like we're
gonna move away and hide.
We can't afford to.
I'll just have to
begin my new attempt
at a world conquest from
this current Devil's Castle!
This from someone
who can't even get
a full-time job?
If you think I plan
to live a peaceful
part-timer's life,
you are dead wrong;
I've got goals.
One of which is to
subjugate this world!
For your information, Hero.
MgRonald's sometimes lets
their part-timers go full-time!
Hear me, Emilia!
I shall become a regular
employee in this world!
And thus, accumulate
wealth and social status.
I will become so
powerful all manner
of humans will kneel before me!
Then I will invade
Ente Isla once more!
[clapping]
[EMILIA] That's ludicrous.
Hmph! Don't feel bad;
I'm sure a mere human like you
has no way of
understanding my lofty aims.
[ASHIYA] I suspect she
understands all too well, Sire.
[EMILIA] Wow, somehow,
I just don't care.
Huh... G' bye,
I'm going home, now.
I have work tomorrow.
But don't get the wrong idea;
if I use my remaining power,
I can kill you any time I want.
Really, then what
are you waiting for?
[EMILIA ] If I use
it all up on you,
I won't be able to
go home to Ente Isla.
As long as you behave,
I'll let you live until
I figure a way out of here.
[EMI] Oh, and in this world,
my name is Emi Yusa.
Try not to forget it.
[EMI] What's with calling
yourself Sadao, anyway?
Nobody in this generation
has that name!
[MAOU] You need to apologize
to all the Sadaos
for that crack!
Hey, Emi.
You've been like really
stressed lately, haven't you?
Wanna grab dinner
and talk about it?
[EMI] Umm... Actually, I can't;
I have something to do tonight.
[RIKA] Do you have a date
and ya didn't tell me about it?
No, it's not like that at all!
[EMI] There is no way
the Devil is living like
a freakin' pauper
"just because."
I can't let him out of my sight.
[MAOU] Aw, come on, man.
Why do I have to go?
[ASHIYA] I cannot
do this alone, Sire!
The task requires
your powers, as well.
We must hurry,
or we'll be too late!
[MAOU] Jeez, it'll be fine.
We got tons of time.
[ASHIYA] This is war, Sire!
Steel yourself!
[EMI] Where are they
headed at this time of day?
Let's get back in line again.
We can each buy
another carton that way.
No, that's against the rules.
Emi. How about grabbing
dinner tonight?
Oh, I can't.
I'm sorry; I've got some
errands I have to run.
[MAOU] Ashiya!
I'm leaving you behind!
I'm not waiting any longer!
It's time for that bath!
[ASHIYA] Please, Sire!
Wait for me!
I just need to lock the door!
[EMI] A bath, as in a bloodbath?
[MAOU] Sweet, made it in time.
[sighs] Ahh...
Wish they'd keep
this place open
twenty-four hours.
You know what,
when I conquer this world,
first thing I'm gonna do
is make sure
bathhouses never close.
[RIKA] Okay, you have to
come out with me tonight.
[EMI] Yeah. Um--
You can't be busy again?
Yeah. I know; I suck.
[RIKA] You are totally putting
misters before sisters!
No, I told you it's
not like that.
[ASHIYA] Sire, please don't!
[MAOU] How can
you not be curious
about this demonic experiment?
[ASHIYA] "Demonic?"
More like insipid!
[MAOU] Whoa, it's
just like Chi said!
You gotta at least try this.
It tastes like melon.
I mean, a little.
[ASHIYA] "Melon" my foot!
[EMI] Maybe I should
just go home.
[ASHIYA]
A cucumber is a cucumber,
whether you put
honey on it or not!
Now, you listen to me, Sire!
Only those with leeway
in their budgets
can afford to take such
risks with their food!
Oh, come on,
can you not find any
"leeway" in your heart?
I do not appreciate
your snarky retorts, at all!
If you're craving melon enough
to wanna mix cucumbers
and honey together,
you're better off
just buying a melon!
Seriously!
What're we looking at?
An earthquake.
[ASHIYA] Don't try
to distract me!
[MAOU] Sheesh, calm down.
[ASHIYA] And don't
you "sheesh" me!
Sheesh you, King Satan!
[MAOU] Heh... Sheesh.
Welcome.
May I have a moment?
Are you ready to order
some food, Miss?
[EMI] I need to
speak with you outside.
To Go order, then.
As soon as
you get off work,
meet me at the intersection
where we first met.
And I'm not taking
no for an answer.
[MAOU] Would you like
to make that a Meal?
Come alone or else.
Okay, we can do that.
Just the burger this time.
Could I get one
Big Mig please? To Go!
I don't plan on
fighting you, either.
So don't chicken out.
Great. Thanks a bunch!
Step to the side, please,
your food will be right out!
Such a pain.
[CHIHO] That customer was
kind of weird, wasn't she?
[MAOU] Sure was.
Takes all kinds, as they say.
[CHIHO] Looked like you two
were talking about something.
Do you know her?
[MAOU] I guess you could say
we have a bit of "history."
Ha! I knew she
smelled fishy!
How come?
First of all she was sort
of pretty, wasn't she?
Did you think
she was pretty? Huh?!
I don't understand why
you're yelling at me.
What's this all about?
It's not like you're my--
Welcome to MgRonald's!
I can take your order
whenever you're ready.
'Kay, I'm headin' out
for the day, Mister Maou!
Hm? Night, Chi. Be careful!
Bye; I'll be back in tomorrow!
Oh, by the way.
[MAOU] Yeah?
Were you all right in
yesterday's earthquake?
[MAOU] Earthquake?
Oh, yeah, I guess there was one.
Some reason my roommate
didn't feel it.
Your who did what?
[MAOU]
"My who did what" what?
You didn't tell me
you had a roommate.
[MAOU] Let's stick
with the earthquake.
Oh, right.
Must've hit my place super hard.
When I got home from school,
all my books and
CDs were on the floor.
It was such a mess.
What? I didn't realize it
was that big; I barely felt it.
Weird.
That's what everyone
at school said, too,
so I guess it was just randomly
focused on where I live, then.
Mister Maou, I almost forgot!
[MAOU] What? What?
[CHIHO] Remember that time--
you told me you have a roommate?
I do.
Might-- this, um--
Might this roommate
be of the girlfriend
roommate persuasion
by any chance at all?
No, it's not a girlfriend.
I'm broke, so I live
with an old serva--
I mean, old friend of mine.
Oh. Well, that's
totally fine, then. Heh.
Thank goodness.
[MAOU] For what?
So, whad'ya
wanna talk about?
I want the answer to
an important question.
The truth.
Would you prefer to stay
in this world forever?
What? No, of course
I wouldn't.
Jeez, where did
that even come from?
[EMI] I've watched your
behavior and attitude at work,
not to mention your crap home
over the last several days.
So now you're stalking me?
[EMI] You haven't
done anything evil,
and you're living a
simple, serious life.
Your manager and your co-workers
all trust you implicitly,
and you deal with customers
confidently and kindly.
You're the perfect
MgRonald's employee.
That's not a
compliment, is it?
I was ready to write
off what you said,
about trying to conquer
this world for yourself,
but now I'm starting
to think there was
some truth behind those words.
Because if you're
willing to spend
the rest of your
life in this world,
then I don't feel
a need to defeat you
just for the sake of it.
Why don't you and
Ashiya just stay here
and conquer stuff?
If telling straight men to live
with other straight men
forever is some sort of
twisted thing you've got,
you need major help, lady.
I think you should
give up on Ente Isla.
Find a new life and a
new enemy here on Earth.
Ha! Not gonna happen.
I told you, I'm going
back to Ente Isla,
and I will subjugate it.
Ugh, he's unbelievable.
Maybe I'm wrong;
maybe he's not the Devil.
[MAOU] A flat tire?
Get it together, Dullahan!
How could you die on me
right after I bought you?!
Jeez, dramatic much?
You know you can fix a flat
for practically nothing,
don't you?
[MAOU] Are you for real?
Then I'll go first
thing in the morning!
I think someone's
shooting at us.
I think you're right.
Blasted right
through that sign!
I didn't say you
could touch me!
Are you seriously
arguing with me right now?
Not bad for a girl.
Give me some credit.
I'm the Hero.
I'll give you credit
if you get off of me.
Eh?! That was your
fault for being weak
and letting me land on you.
[MAOU] It's early
enough for there to be
plenty of people
at the train station.
How fast can you run?
I bet I'm faster than you
since you're used to
riding a bike all the time.
Race ya there! Come on!
[MAOU] I guess they're not
following us out this far, huh?
We should be safe now.
What do you think
that was about?
[MAOU] I dunno, but it
was no ordinary sniper.
Those bullets were
made of magical energy.
[EMI] Magic?
So what's that mean?
We're dealing with
someone fairly powerful.
And that someone knows
who you and I really are.
But who could
that possibly be?
[MAOU] A mystery sniper
at the precise place
a demon and a hero meet up?
The logical assumption is
they've gotta be from Ente Isla.
Ya see the kind of
trouble you get me into?
Wait, you think
this is my fault?
[MAOU] If you'd picked
a safer time and place,
this wouldn't have happened.
So yes, I think
it is your fault.
[EMI] Wrong!
It's totally your fault
for working so late!
[MAOU] Well, we could
have met in the afternoon.
[EMI] I have to work
in the afternoon, genius!
[MAOU] That's not
really my problem, is it?
[EMI] Hey! Where're you--?
I gotta work early.
I'm heading home to crash.
[EMI] What?
You're going off alone?
[MAOU] That's the plan.
You probably oughtta
be careful out here.
See ya!
Now whaddaya want?
You planning to go
on a night raid?
Something like that?
No. Nothing
like that; promise.
Then what's the big idea?
My landlady lives in the
apartment right next door to us!
I'd rather avoid
running into her,
so no making a scene, okay?
Jeez. What is it?
[EMI] This makes me
wanna puke just asking.
And more importantly, it's a
breach of my faith, but still.
Did you come here just
to try and piss me off?
Um. Would you--
[MAOU] What?
Would... you let me
stay the night with you?
When we ran,
I dropped my wallet.
[ASHIYA] Emilia the Hero!
[MAOU] Keep your pants on;
she doesn't have the energy
to fight at the moment.
Unacceptable!
You are the King of Darkness;
you cannot simply
"party the night away"
with some fucshia-haired floozy!
We got shot at earlier
tonight with magical bullets.
Both of us were targeted, too.
No, my Liege!
[MAOU] Yes, and she
dropped her wallet
while we were running away.
So, apparently she lives
too far away to walk.
Guess having a bike is
better than you thought, huh?
I'm confused, Sire.
Are you saying she's
spending the night with us?
That's what I'm saying;
come on in, Emi.
Um, thank you
for having me.
[MAOU] You can sit wherever.
And FYI, don't expect
any luxuries or anything,
like a bed to sleep on.
[EMI] No worries; I won't.
What kind of
disrespectful attitude
is that in the face of King
Satan's act of benevolence?
[MAOU] Shut it, Ashiya,
or the landlady will show up.
Here, Emi. You can use this.
[EMI] That's the
same detergent I use.
[MAOU] If you want a pillow,
use some of those magazines.
Suppose I can lend you
a little money for now, too.
Use it to get out of
here on the first bus.
'Kay.
[ASHIYA] His Evilness
graciously lends you
that money from his
less-than-meager savings.
Treat it with reverence!
You've made yourselves clear!
I'll leave in the morning,
thanks for the loan.
Goodnight!
I dislike this one.
[MAOU] We should turn in, too.
Right.
But know that I shan't
let my guard down!
So none of your funny business!
[EMI] This is the worst.
How did I end up here?
[MAOU] Y'know,
we were pretty miserable
at first, too, remember?
[ASHIYA] Yes, Sire.
[MAOU] And we got
through it okay
because there were two of us.
But Emi doesn't have anyone.
[ASHIYA] Is it just me, King
Satan, or are you growing soft?
[MAOU] Who's this? Earthquakes?
There are more of them coming?
Oh. I've got a
text from Chi, too.
"There's going to
be another earthquake.
What do I do?" Weird.
Something wrong, Sire?
[MAOU] What's going on?