Hey, let's go!
I'm happy as can be
Let's go walking, you and me
Ready, set, come on, let's go!
Over the hill, across the field
Through the tunnel we'll go
We'll run across the bridge
And down the bumpy gravel road
Creep beneath the spider's web
Ready, set, let's go!
Hey, let's go!
I'm happy as can be
Let's go walking, you and me
Ready, set, come on, let's go!
The foxes and the badgers too
All come out to play
They all want to explore
The deep and wonderful woods all day
Look at all my many friends
Ready, set, let's go!
Hey dad, want some caramel?
Thanks. How you doing back there?
Fine.
Are you tired? Oop!
Mmm-mmm.
We're almost there.
Mei, hide.
Whoops. I thought that was a policeman.
Hi!
Hello there. Are your parents around?
We're your new neighbors.
Great. Thanks.
Hello! Hi, we're the Kusakabes!
We're moving in down the street.
Why don't you and your family stop by sometime?
Okey, sure. Good to meet you.
Uh!
Hey, thanks a lot.
This is it, girls.
Wait up!
Here you go.
Mei, look at this bridge.
A bridge?
There's a fish! Oh, look! There's another one!
So, how do you like the new place?
Dad, it's perfect.
Look at this. A tunnel of trees.
Oh, wow! Look!
Dad, hurry!
Wow! It's creepy.
Creepy!
It looks like it could be haunted.
What, haunted?
Whoa.
Look. It's rotten.
It's collapsing!
Mei, look at that.
Huh?
Look.
Wow! It's huge, isn't it?
Ah-choo!
Dad, what's that big tree?
Uh, that's a camphor tree.
A camphor tree.
Camphor tree!
Don't forget to take your shoes off, girls.
Huh?
Whoa!
An acorn.
Let me see.
Another one!
Here's one.
Out of the way, Mei.
I can't close the door with you there.
Acorns.
Dad, acorns are falling from the ceiling.
Falling from the ceiling.
Hmm.
Maybe squirrels live here.
Squirrels?
I think rats eat acorns. Maybe they're rats.
No! Squirrels are better!
Mister, where do you want your radio?
Oh, right, the radio. In here's good, I guess.
Satsuki, open the back of the house?
Okay.
Can you find the back door?
Of course!
Come on!
Hey, wait for me!
Well, hurry it up, then.
Let's go.
Hmph!
The bath.
Yep.
I think they're gone.
Hey, you found the bath.
Something's running around in here.
More squirrels?
I don't think so.
They're not bugs or mice either.
They were black and they were all over the place.
Hmm. Let's have a look.
Ah.
So?
It's probably just some soot gremlins.
What do you mean, "gremlins"? Like the ones in my book?
Well, it could be ghosts,
but ghosts don't usually like to
come out on nice days like this.
Normally, you can't see soot gremlins, but once in awhile,
when you go from bright places to dark
ones, you catch a glimpse.
So that's it.
Come out, come out...
Wherever you are!
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
Hey, I need your help. It looks like somebody's
hidden the stairs to the top of the house.
What?
Can you find the stairs and open the windows up there?
Yeah!
Wail for me!
Nope.
The toilet!
Not here.
Nothing here.
Nope.
Ahh!
Nope. Hey!
Mei, I found the stairs.
It's pitch-black.
Maybe it's the soot gremlins.
An acorn.
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
Hmph.
Ahh!
We know you're in here, soot gremlins.
Come on out.
Hey!
Huh?
Okay, lift.
Dad, come here! There's definitely
something weird in this house!
That's great.
I've always wanted to live in a haunted
house ever since I was a little boy.
Oh!
Ahh!
I caught one! Satsuki, look!
Ah!
Hi.
Mei?
Oh.
Whoa. Hey!
What a ball of energy!
This is our neighbor. She takes care of this house.
She said you can call her "Granny" if you'd like.
I'm Satsuki, and that's Mei. Nice to meet you.
Well, it's nice to meet you, too.
What nice manners you have.
I'm sorry I didn't have time to
clean up more before you got here.
No, it's fine.
We've been busy in the rice fields,
but I did manage to keep the
place well-dusted, as you can see.
Mei, your hands are filthy. What on earth did you do?
I caught a soot gremlin, but he got away.
Ahh! Your feet!
Mine are black, too!
Ah...
You've got soot sprites in your house.
Soot sprites? The black puff balls? About this big?
They scurry everywhere when you enter a room?
That's right.
They live in old, empty houses
and run all over the place, covering everything with dirt.
I used to be able to see them when I was your age.
So you've seen them, too. That's very interesting.
So they're a kind of ghost, then?
Don't worry, dear. They're nothing to be afraid of.
If they decide you're nice people, they won't harm you,
and after a while, they'll just go away.
I bet they're up in the rafters right now,
having a talk about whether or not they should move out.
Hear that? They're gonna move out.
I don't want them to leave.
What if a huge one came chasing after you?
So what? I'm not afraid.
Right. Then you can go to the bathroom
alone in the middle of the night.
Come on, girls.
Let's get to work. Who'd like to fetch water for the pump?
I'll go get it.
I'll go, too!
Mei, wait there, okay?
Did you catch a fish?
Granny, the pump's working!
Keep pumping!
Don't stop until the water gets cold.
Okay.
Oh. Hello again. Can I help you?
Eh... My... mom said to give this to Granny.
Oh. What is it?
Mmm.
Hmm?
Mmm! Eh...
Hey, wait! What is this?
Is that Kanta?
Hey, you in there!
Your house is haunted!
Kanta!
Mmm.
Satsuki, I acted just like that when I was a boy.
I hate boys, but I'm glad he brought this cake you made.
It's great, Granny.
Eat all you like.
Thanks, moving man!
Thanks for everything, Granny.
Good-bye, Granny!
Dad, this house is too old. I think it's gonna fall down.
That would be a problem, since we just moved in here.
Huh?
Everybody, try laughing.
Then whatever scares you will go away.
But, Dad, I'm not scared.
What? I'm not scared.
One, two, one, two, one, two.
That's it. Stamp that dirt out, girls. That's it.
One, two...
Okay. That's all the chores.
You're done.
Yay!
Ready? Hold on!
Who-o-oa!
Whoo-ooo!
Granny!
Hi, Granny!
Good afternoon!
Hello there, Kusakabes! Where are you headed?
We're going to visit Mom at the hospital!
That's good! Say hi!
Tell her I hope she's feeling better.
We will!
Mmm.
Hey, this way. Whoa!
Hey, Dad. There it is.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
Hello, dear.
Mommy!
Hi, Mei. It's so good to see you.
Daddy kept getting lost the whole way here, Mom.
Oh, he did? No school?
No, it's a rice-planting day.
Oh, is that so?
Hey, Mom, Dad's talking to the doctor.
I am so happy to see you girls.
So how do you like it in the country? Have you settled in?
Yeah.
Hmm?
Mei's scared...
A haunted house?
Mmm-hmm.
Mommy, do you like haunted houses?
Of course. I'll have to get better
soon so I can meet some ghosts.
See that, Mei?
Mmm-hmm.
Mei was worried that you wouldn't
come home if the house was haunted.
Do you two like it?
Yeah!
I'm not scared at all.
Oh, what cute hair. Did you do this, Satsuki?
Mmm-hmm.
It's very nice, huh, Mei?
What a lucky girl you are.
Yeah, but she yells at me a lot.
That's because you never sit still.
Let's see your hair, Satsuki.
You sure it isn't a little too short?
No, I like it this way, Mom.
Brush my hair! Brush mine!
Wait your turn, Mei.
Your hair will never cooperate.
It's exactly like my hair when I was your age.
Do you think it will start cooperating soon?
I want it to look like yours.
I think it will.
You and I are a lot alike, Satsuki.
Mom looked great, didn't she, Dad?
Yeah, she did, her doctor said she
should be able to come home soon.
So she'll be home tomorrow?
There she goes again with tomorrow.
Tomorrow might be a bit soon.
Mom said she was gonna sleep in my bed with me.
I thought you weren't scared to sleep alone.
Can't you sleep by yourself?
She's the one who's scared, not me.
Hey, Dad! Look, it's morning!
Umph!
Hey, wake up!
Sorry. I overslept again.
I have to take lunch to school today.
Oh, no. I forgot all about that.
That's okay. I'm making lunch for everyone.
Hey, it's burning!
I'm coming. Just a minute.
I'm making this one for you, Mei.
I get one?
Mei, sit down and eat.
There you go. Wrap it up so it stays fresh. Okay?
Satsuki!
That's Michiko.
Hi!
So, you made a friend already, did you?
Satsuki, time for school!
She's walking to school with me.
I gotta go.
See you later!
Have a nice day!
Hi, Michiko.
Hi. Ready for school?
Yep.
Hey, Dad.
Do I look like a big girl?
You do. Are you going somewhere?
I'm just off to run some errands.
Dad, is it lunchtime yet?
What? We just ate breakfast.
Dad, you be the flower shop. Okay?
Hey, tadpoles.
What a stupid bucket.
Huh?
Acorn.
Ha!
Huh?
Hey!
Bleh!
Ahh!
Hey!
Ahh! Ahh!
Whoa!
Ahh...
Ah-choo!
Who are you? A great big soot gremlin?
To-to-ro!
Totoro?
Is that what your name is? Totoro?
Totoro.
Yep, that's your name, all right.
Mmm. Totoro.
Bye.
See you later!
I'm home!
Hi there.
Wow. Is it that late already?
Where's Mei?
Did she like her lunch box?
We haven't eaten yet. She's running
around with that lunch box all day.
Mei!
Mei?
Hey, Dad! Come here!
I found Mei's hat!
Mei! Mei!
Hmm? Hmm.
Hey, Mei, wake up!
What do you think you're doing, sleeping out here?
Totoro?
Where's Totoro?
Maybe you were dreaming.
No, I saw Totoro.
Totoro?
You mean a troll, like the one in your storybook?
Mmm-hmm. But he called himself Totoro.
He was furry, with a great big mouth.
There was a little one, and a bigger one,
and a huge one that kept falling asleep.
There you are.
Wow. This would make a great secret hiding place.
Dad, Mei said that she saw a Totoro here.
A Totoro?
Mmm-hmm.
This way!
Hey, wait up!
Huh?
Here?
Mmm-mmm.
Last time the tunnel led to Totoro's tree.
I didn't see another path to take.
Hey, where are you going?
Mei, come back!
Quit laughing! I really did see Totoro!
I'm not lying.
Mmm.
Mei?
It's not a lie, Dad.
Hmm. Don't worry, Mei.
Satsuki and I believe you, and I bet I know what happened.
You must have met one of the spirits of the forest.
That means you're a very lucky girl.
But you can't always see the spirits.
You can only see them when they want you to.
Let's give the forest spirits a proper greeting.
A greeting?
Of course. Come on. Let's go.
Oh, Mei, you're getting heavy.
Dad, there's that big camphor tree.
It's incredible.
That's it!
That's Totoro's tree?
Yeah!
Come on, Dad! Can't you go any faster?
Whoa.
Totoro's hole is gone.
Are you sure it was here?
Mmm-hmm.
Dad, she says the hole disappeared.
Then, right now the forest spirits don't want to be seen.
But, Dad, I want to see them, too.
Maybe you will, if you're lucky.
Mmm. Magnificent tree.
It's been around since long ago,
back in the time when trees and people used to be friends.
When I saw this tree, I knew this would
be a good place for our family to live.
And I think it will make your mother feel right at home.
So, let's give this tree a nice
greeting and go eat our lunch.
I want to write Mom a letter and tell her about this.
I will, too!
Attention!
Thank you for watching over Mei
and making us feel so welcome here.
Please continue to look after us.
Last one home's a rotten egg!
Hey, no fair!
Wait!
Uh!
Hurry it up!
Wail for me!
Dear Mom: We had an exciting day today.
Mei met a big forest spirit called Totoro.
I hope I'll be able to see him someday, too.
Kanta, hurry up, or you'll be late for school.
Yeah.
Back to work.
Oh.
Mei?
Miss Hara!
Yes, Satsuki?
Uh, my sister's here.
Her sister?
Granny, what's wrong?
I don't know.
She said she wouldn't stop crying
unless I brought her to you.
She said that? Mei, be reasonable.
You know you had to stay with Granny in the day.
Because, I have school and Dad's
teaching at the university.
I only have two more hours of school to go.
Can't you just stay with Granny until then?
She's been so good up till now. Weren't you, Mei?
Well, I'll talk to my teacher and see what we can do.
Satsuki's mom is in the hospital,
so her sister Mei is going to
stay with us today, okay, class?
Let's make her feel welcome.
Yes, ma'am.
What are you drawing, Mei?
It's a big Totoro.
Shh. Mei, try to keep quiet, will you?
Mmm-hmm.
Bye, Mei!
Come again soon!
I have to skip our club meeting, Michiko.
I'll let everyone know. Bye!
Hurry up, Mei. It's gonna rain.
Okay.
Ah! Here it comes!
Here it comes!
Come on.
I didn't even cry. That's good, huh?
Hmm.
Yeah, but we're not home yet.
We'd like to share your roof for a
while, sir, if you don't mind.
Mmm.
Huh?
Don't you...
Mmm. Mmm!
Mmm!
Hey!
That was lucky, wasn't it?
Mmm-hmm.
This umbrella has holes.
Hmm.
Dad left his umbrella here.
I better take it to him.
I wanna go, too.
What? I left it.
What kind of fool forgets his
umbrella at school when it's raining?
Hey!
I bet you were swinging it around and you broke it.
No, I didn't.
Ahh.
Hello! Is anyone home?
Oh, Satsuki and Mei. Come in. Granny!
Thanks for watching Mei today.
Sorry we couldn't keep her happy.
Oh. I wanted to give back this
umbrella that Kanta lent us.
What? He lent you this? Oh, my. Look how beat up it is.
Mei was walking home from school with me.
So, it was really nice of him to help us out.
Tell him thank you.
He must have been drenched.
That's okay.
Kanta is such a dirty kid.
He can always use a good drenching.
Are you off to meet your dad at the bus stop?
Yes, he forgot his umbrella.
Such good kids.
Bye, girls.
Bye!
Who was at the door, Kanta?
Beats me.
There's the bus, Mei!
Are you getting on?
Drive on.
Satsuki, Dad wasn't on the bus.
He'll be on the next one for sure.
Do you want to go back to Granny's and wait there?
What's the matter?
What is it, Mei? Are you sleepy?
I knew this would happen.
Don't you want to wait at Granny's?
Mmm-mmm.
It's okay, Mei. He'll be here soon.
That bus sure is late, huh?
Here.
Totoro?
Oh, wait a minute.
Here. Try this.
Hurry. Mei's slipping.
Hold it over your head. Like this.
Oh.
Here comes the bus.
Huh?
Well, Mei, so much for bringing Dad his umbrella.
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
Drive on.
My train was delayed, so I had to wait for the next bus.
Were you worried?
Totoro came back, Dad! I saw him!
We saw a cat bus, too!
What?
It was huge!
With eyes like this.
It was great!
I saw Totoro! I saw him!
I saw him, too!
Hey, Dad, pick us up.
Come on, Dad.
We had such a weird, mysterious, spectacular day.
My heart is still pounding.
Totoro gave us a wonderful present.
It was wrapped in a bamboo leaf
and tied with a ribbon made of grass.
As soon as we got home, we opened it.
It was filled with acorns.
Ahh.
"We wanted to grow a beautiful forest with the acorns,
" so we planted them IN your garden out back, but..."
... they just won't grow.
Mei watches them all day, every day,
waiting for them to sprout,
it's starting to make her crabby.
Here's a picture of Mei as a crab.
Summer vacation is almost here,
and I can't wait to play outside with you.
Please get well soon. Love, Satsuki.
Get ready, and... up!
Lights out, girls.
Wait, Dad.
Do you think that they'll sprout tomorrow?
I don't know.
You should ask the Totoro. He would know.
Good night, girls.
Mei.
That's where we planted the acorns.
Ahh!
Ow!
Yay! We did it! We did it!
Yay!
Mei, we're the wind!
Mmm...
Where'd the tree go?
Ahh!
They're growing! We did it!
We did it!
I thought it was a dream!
But it wasn't!
I thought it was a dream! We did it!
We did it!
Mr. Kusakabe? Telegram!
Mr. Kusakabe?
A telegram for you.
Huh. No one's home.
Granny!
I'm over here.
This one's ready to eat.
What about this one, Granny?
Try it.
Wow, Granny. Your garden is just like a market.
We've picked enough, haven't we? Let's take a rest.
Mmm. Nice and cold.
Mark, get set, go!
It's delicious.
I'm glad you like it. They're very good for you.
They've soaked up lots of vitamins and sunshine.
Would they help Mom get better?
Of course they would.
If your mom eats my vegetables,
I bet she'd get well right away.
That's great, Granny. Mom's coming home on Saturday.
She's going to sleep with me in my bed.
Oh, good! She's finally leaving the hospital, is she?
No. The doctor wants her to get used
to the new house a little at a time.
She goes back on Monday.
Is that so?
We'll feed her lots of my vegetables while she's here.
I'll give her the corn that I picked.
That will make her better.
I bet that will do her wonders.
Yep.
Here. The postman left us your telegram.
A telegram?
What should I do with it? Dad won't be home till evening.
Better open it. Might be an emergency.
Mmm-hmm.
"Please contact Shichikokuyama."
Shichikokuyama! It's from Mom's hospital!
Something must have happened to her.
We have to get to the hospital right away, Granny.
Okay. Calm down.
First, we need to get in touch with your father.
I know his phone number at the
university, but we don't have a phone.
Kanta, take Satsuki to your uncle's
house and let her use the phone.
Mmm-hmm.
Mei, you need to stay here with me!
Mei, go back and stay with Granny!
Uh!
Hello? I'd like to place a long-distance call, please.
It's to my dad at Tokyo 31-13-82.
Right.
Now, that's a nice girl, eh, Kanta?
Hello?
Yes.
Hello? I need to speak to my dad
in the archaeology department.
I mean, I need to speak to Mr. Kusakabe.
My name is Satsuki Kusakabe.
Hello, Dad? Is that you? It's Satsuki.
What's wrong?
We got a telegram.
You're to call Mom's doctor at the hospital.
What? The hospital?
Okay. I'll call them right away.
Did something happen to her? Do you think she's okay?
Let's not worry.
I'll call the hospital,
and I'll call you right back. Okay?
Yeah.
Wait by the phone.
Mmm-hmm.
I need to hang up now. Okay?
Excuse me, is it okay if I wait here?
My dad's going to call me back.
Of course. Make yourself at home.
Satsuki!
Back off! Don't touch my corn!
It's for my mommy!
Too bad! She needs it to make her better.
Mei, the doctor said that Mom's not doing well.
So she doesn't get to come home this weekend.
No fair!
It can't be helped, Mei.
What if she came and it made her worse?
It's not fair!
Mei, we just have to wait a little longer.
No!
You want her to die, Mei?
Is that what you want?
No!
You're such a baby! Just grow up!
Come on, Mei.
She's so mean!
Come on, girls. Let's put the laundry away.
Oh, don't be sad. Granny's here to help.
Don't worry. Your father is going to stop by the hospital.
The doctors say your mom just has a cold.
She should be home next Saturday.
This is just like last time.
They said Mom just had a little
cold, she'd be home in a few days.
Granny, what will we do if she dies?
Satsuki!
Maybe she's dead already.
Now, don't say that, sweetheart.
How could she ever leave such sweet girls like you?
Oh, don't cry.
Don't cry. It's all right.
I'll stay here until your father comes home. Okay? Okay?
Mei!
Did she come back?
No.
She wasn't at the bus stop?
Let's think.
Do you know where else she might have gone?
I yelled at her this morning. She wanted Mom to come home.
Granny, I bet she went to see Mom at the hospital!
You think she'd try to walk to the hospital?
Why, that's a three-hour walk even for grown-ups.
I'll go look.
Kanta! Hurry! Run on home and get your father!
Mei's disappeared, and we need all the help we can get!
I shouldn't have yelled at her. This is all my fault.
Mei!
Excuse me, mister! Hello!
Yeah?
I'm looking for my sister.
Did you happen to see a little girl pass this way?
Let's see. Uh, a little girl?
Mmm, I don't think so. I would have noticed.
I'll try the other road.
Are you sure that this is the way she came?
I don't know.
Mei!
Stop! Please, stop!
Oh! Are you crazy?
I'm looking for my little sister.
Have you seen a girl walking this way?
Is she lost?
I think she's trying to walk to the hospital.
She's only four years old.
Oh. I didn't see her. Did you??
No. We just came from the hospital,
and there was no sign of a little girl on the road.
Okay. Thanks.
Wait. Where'd you say you're from?
From Matsugo.
Matsugo! Ho!
A four-year-old couldn't walk this far.
Good luck. I hope you find her.
Satsuki!
Kanta!
Find her?
No.
I guess you didn't, either.
Mmm-mmm.
My dad's got a bunch of people looking for her.
I could ride my bike to the hospital for you.
You should go back home.
Check all around.
I'm sure that Mei got lost on her way to the hospital.
A little while ago, they found a sandal in the pond.
They don't know for sure it's Mei's sandal!
Did you find her yet?
We'll check the irrigation ditch.
On the far end.
It's much deeper over there. You should try there first!
Are there more poles?
Huh?
It's Satsuki.
Here. Is this Mei's?
It's not hers.
Oh!
Ohh...
Oh, thank goodness.
I was positively certain that sandal belonged to Mei.
All right. Granny just got carried away.
Hey! It's not her sandal!
All right everyone, I know you've spent a lot
of time here, but we still need your help.
Satsuki!
Please.
Let me in to see Totoro. Mei's lost.
It's getting dark, and she's out there all alone.
Please let me in to see him. It's an emergency.
Totoro!
Totoro, Mei's lost. I looked everywhere for
her, but I couldn't find her.
Please help me. I have to find her.
I'm sure she's scared half to death by now.
I don't know where else to turn.
No one else can see it, can they?
Huh?
FOREST-SWAMP
CEMETERY-SHRINE
MEI
Mei.
Mei!
The trees are parting!
Satsuki!
Where are you?
Mei!
Satsuki!
Oh! You're okay.
I'm sorry.
Were you trying to take your corn to Mom at the hospital?
Mmm-hmm.
HOSPITAL
You're going to take us to the hospital?
Thank you!
I'm sorry. I don't know why the hospital sent a telegram.
It's just a cold.
I hope it didn't upset them too much.
I've caused enough grief already.
When they see you're all right, they'll be fine.
We'll just wait a little longer for a weekend together.
Don't worry. We've made it this far.
The girls act so strong,
but I think it's harder than they let on.
Especially Satsuki.
She tries to act so adult.
That's true.
I can't wait until I get better.
When I get home, I'm going to spoil the girls rotten.
Look at Mom. She's laughing.
Everything must be okay.
Yeah.
I'm going to hurry up and get well!
That's the spirit. Huh?
Who left this?
What is it?
I thought I saw Satsuki and Mei
smiling at us from up in that tree.
It sounds crazy, but maybe you did.
Look at this.
"For Mommy."
Totoro, Totoro
Who leaves the seeds
For you to find
Follow them and you will see
A treasure there
Then plant the seeds
And help them grow
It may seem like a dream
Things are not what they seem
Now begins a new adventure
For you!
And you'll be with To-to-ro, Totoro!
To-to-ro! Totoro!
Living in the forest trees,
For such a very, very long time!
There you'll be with To-to-ro, Totoro!
To-to-ro, Totoro!
You only see him when your very young,
A magical adventure for you!
It's magic for you.
Rain tumbles down...
The bus is late.
Suddenly, a furry wet giant
Is by your side!
Don't be afraid...
Just open wide!
Your umbrella for him,
Watch him play in the rain!
Now begins a new adventure
For you!
And you'll be with To-to-ro, Totoro!
To-to-ro, Totoro!
And on a moonlit night,
He plays a magic flute in the sky!
There you'll be with To-to-ro, Totoro!
To-to-ro, Totoro!
You only see him when your very young,
A magical adventure for you!
It's magic for you.