There is evil lurking in the
shadows of this world--
in the form of beings
called Crimson Denizens.
They've come from an adjacent
world, the Crimson Realm,
to collect precious power
of existence from the humans.
They slip into day-to-day life.
Then they slowly
begin to devour that life.
However, none of the humans
ever seem to notice
what's happening.
Thanks.
Next up, Sakai!
Yes sir!
Father came back from Tokyo
and told us about the sights--
Hey Sakai... what's up?!
Hey Ike.
What's up?
I thought you had to stay
after for cleaning duty?
Nah, I got someone
to cover for me.
I have a mock exam
at cram school today.
Jeez, man.
You're already
prepping for college?
I've gotta do what I can
to keep my parents happy,
otherwise my allowance
ends up suffering.
So... What're you up to?
I don't have any plans
so I guess I'll go down to
the station and check
out the new CD releases.
Have fun.
So Sakai is the guy you're
crushing on, right Kazumi?
How'd you know that?
We've been friends forever.
I can totally tell you like him!
No, I mean, it's just--
You don't have
to hide it from me.
You know, if you really are
interested in Sakai then we
might be able to
help each other out.
Huh?
I don't understand--how so?
C'mon, Kazumi,
this is your chance!
I guess I can't depend
on her to be much help.
I'll just have to work
it out on my own.
I got this!
Hello.
So, what's up?
Hey, where is Ike any way--
why isn't he with you?
He had to go to cram school
for some kinda mock exam.
Why'd you ask?
No reason.
It's just you guys
are always together.
It's not like we're attached
at the hip or anything.
I know this is out of the
blue but I was wondering if
you knew whether or
not Ike has a steady girlfriend.
Well, no I don't
think that he does.
Oh, okay.
I gotta go by the station
so I guess I'll see you later.
Cool.
See ya later!
I get it.
She's got a crush on Ike.
Don't run!
You'll spill your soda!
Be careful, kid!
What the--What's going on?
Whoa.
Everyone's frozen!
Okay!
The preparations are complete!
There aren't that
many humans here
but I suppose it'll
be enough to suffice.
Time to dig in.
Yummy!
Delicious!
They're so tasty!
You should know better than
to talk with your mouth full!
Mind your manners, young lady!
Yes, ma'am.
What-- no!
Hirai!
Who the hell is this kid?
I'm not sure,
but he's definitely not
a Crimson Denizen.
But if not then why's he able
to move around inside the Seal?
He must be a Mystes!
What's a Mystes?
You mean one of those Torches
that has a treasure inside?
That's right and
this one is very special.
We haven't brought the master
any souvenirs in a while.
This one should make him happy.
Yay!
We got a present for the master!
I got ya!
It's time to eat!
Who did that?!
Who is this girl?
So what do you think, Alastor?
I don't think they're
Crimson Denizens.
It appears they're just Rinne.
That pendant just talked!
How dare you cut off my hand!
I'll crush you!
No, please, don't!
Looks like that body was
nothing more than a shell.
It must have escaped
at the last second.
Well, it's gotta be
around here somewhere.
That's a Mystes, isn't it?
Yes.
And it seems to be
a unique one at that.
Who're you?
What are you doing?!
She hit me.
I've been cut.
You must be the Flaming Haired
and Blazing Eyed Hunter.
You're the Flame Haze
who's contracted to Alastor,
the Flame of Heaven.
Yep, that's me.
What're you gonna do about it?
My master will
be livid when he finds
out you've ruined our plans.
I'm not too worried.
He's going to be taking his
last breath very soon.
Damn you.
But first things first.
You'll breathe your last
breath before I go for his.
Look.... that must
be its true form!
Behind you!
I shouldn't have
let it get away.
Judging from the way those
Rinne were talking there's
someone powerful behind this.
There's only one
way to find out.
We'll have to hunt
down their Crimson Lord.
But before we do that.
Please help me!
It hurts!
Can you call an
ambulance for me?!
Shut up!
Shut up, you big crybaby!
Would you quit your whining
and get over it already?!
You're so cruel.
Be careful, you don't want
to see her when she's angry.
Look, if you were
human you would
have already died
from that wound.
"If I was human"?!
I've got to hurry and
try to stop all the bleeding!
Please help me!
I'm not bleeding.
What is this?!
Is this some kind of dream?!
I'm on fire!
Get it off!
What the hell's going on?!
It's time to rebuild.
Hirai!
She's come back.
Oh, thank goodness.
That should about do
it for the Torches.
I'll use a couple
to rebuild the city.
That's fine.
I still can't believe
how much those Rinne ate.
I guess their
master must require
a lot of power of existence.
Okay.
All done.
No one even noticed
what happened.
How's that possible?
Wait up, Hirai!
I'll walk you home!
What is that?
It looks like a flame.
Hirai.
He's gone.
Where'd he go?
No way!
Hey!
Hold on a minute!
You wanna tell me
what that was all about?!
That little boy just
disappeared into thin air!
And I can see this
blue flame burning inside--
Would you just shut up already?!
Alastor how should
I dispose of it?
You can't be serious!
We mustn't destroy a Mystes.
That would be careless.
I know that's normally the case
but this one's a major pain.
Why don't you just
tell it the truth?
That should be
enough to shut it up.
Why do you keep talking about me
like I'm some
kind object or thing?
Because you are no
longer a human being.
You ARE a thing.
The creatures I fought
back there are called Rinne.
They're basically the lackeys
of Crimson Denizens.
They come to this
world to collect
power of existence,
a type of energy.
They do that by eating humans.
Once a human is eaten by a
Rinne their life is terminated,
they simply cease to exist.
That's right.
And if too many humans
disappear at once it throws off
the world's balance so we
place Torches to fill the void.
What's a Torch?
The remnants of the
person who's been killed.
Like you--you're a Torch.
The real you was
killed so now all that's
left are the remnants
of your existence.
But that's impossible.
Look for yourself.
You can see your
own flame, can't you?
Don't worry;
you're not the only one.
Anybody who has that blue
flame is a Torch just like you.
They're placeholders
for the people
whose existence has
been eaten by Rinne.
Since they're only
temporary replacements,
their flame will
start to dim and
then when it burns out
completely, they'll disappear.
What?
They will leave this world.
And that's my explanation.
But does that mean
I'm already dead?
Hey, wait!
Why do you insist
on following me?
I'm not following you.
I live on this
side of the bridge.
Right.
I can't believe I'm dead.
Yuji Sakai is no
longer alive and
I'm just the shell that's left.
Damn it... I just can't wrap
my head around it.
Can I ask you something?
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
I've answered enough questions!
Are you a human being?!
Tell me!
No I'm not--I'm a Flame Haze.
A Fl--what?
I am a Flame Haze.
I hunt Crimson Denizens
who've killed humans
to consume their
power of existence ok?
She replaces those
killed with a Torch
so the world remains in balance.
Without Flame Hazes, Crimson
Denizens would run rampant
killing even more
humans than they do now.
So you're a Flame Haze.
I am so sorry that
I failed you, Master.
I never meant to cause you to
lose one of your favorite Rinne.
There's no need for you
to apologize, Marianne.
It wasn't your fault.
The two of you were up against a
particularly strong Flame Haze.
I should thank you for
finding a Mystes for me.
That's a fantastic prize
you've found, my dear.
But I didn't bring it back;
I let it get away.
If you'll give me
another chance I'll
hunt down that
Mystes for you, Master.
While I have no doubt that
you would, it isn't necessary.
We mustn't rush into this.
We must think it through
and act carefully my dear.
We can't afford to be
reckless when dealing
with the Flame of
Heaven's Flame Haze.
Yes, Master.
Marianne.
Look at the Crystal Altar.
Isn't it beautiful?
It's absolutely breathtaking.
Let's enjoy this moment.
We should cherish
our time together and
not worry about
that silly Flame Haze.
Yuji!
Your breakfast is ready!
I'll be down in a sec.
As a mother, I want
the best for my family...
That's why I shop at
the Misaki City Market...
I was starting to get worried.
It's not like you to sleep in.
And yesterday you went straight
to bed as soon as you got home.
Is there something wrong?
No, I just had a rough day.
You're looking at a close-up
of the Gobi Desert
in the middle of a sandstorm--
let's see if we can
get a closer look!
Oh wow, the Gobi Desert?
That's where your
father is right now.
Wouldn't it be funny
if we saw him on TV?
Yeah.
Well, Mom seems to be fine.
I was worried she
might be a Torch too.
I wonder how she and Dad would
feel if they found
out that I'm really dead?
I guess it would feel like
they never had a child.
It's better that they
forget I ever existed.
Then they won't
end up being hurt.
It's still so hard to believe
that I'm not alive anymore.
I'm not even the
real Yuji Sakai.
Yuji.
Are you sure everything's okay?
Yeah, everything's
just fine, Mom.
I'd better go.
My homeroom teacher
will write me up if I'm late.
Thanks for breakfast.
I'll see you tonight.
Have a good day!
I feel bad lying to her
but if I told her the
truth she'd be upset.
If I'm just a place holder
for the real Yuji Sakai
then why do I have to deal
with all these emotions?
I don't get it.
What are you doing here?
The Crimson Denizens are
going to come looking for you.
I figured I should probably keep
an eye on you in the meantime.
Sorry, pal.
But that's what happens
when you're a unique Torch.
Don't worry;
I'll watch out for you.
Thanks.
I remember that Rinne thing
called me a Mystes yesterday.
What's that mean?
Impressive, you
have quite a memory.
Okay, how do I put this?
A Mystes is a special kind of
Torch-- one that carries a
Treasure Tool within it that was
created by a Crimson Denizen.
Do what?
You heard me.
Whenever a Mystes' flame
burns out that Treasure Tool
is transferred to a new Torch--
creating a new Mystes.
The best way to describe
it is it's like a moving
treasure chest.
But why's it in me?
How the heck should I know?!
Like I said, these treasures
move from Torch to Torch.
The enemy will likely
come looking for you
before your flame burns
out so they can reclaim it.
Before my flame burns out.
Hey.
How can you be
so sure that I'm dead?
You're a Torch and a Mystes.
But I still have
the same thoughts and
emotions that I
did when I was alive.
'Cause you're his remnants
that were left behind.
That makes sense.
This city is strange.
I've never seen so
many Torches in one place.
It is rather odd, isn't it?
Why does that matter?
Hirai!
Her flame, it's so weak.
Yeah, it doesn't
have much time left.
But why?!
She was just
attacked yesterday?!
Those Rinne were
on a rampage yesterday.
They must've eaten most
of her power of existence.
Hirai!
Hey Hirai!
Good morning!
Do you mind if I walk with you?
I don't mind.
What's happened to her?
She's so different now.
It probably won't even
make it through the day.
It's not right.
Isn't there anything we can do?
'Fraid not.
That's all that's left of her.
You know she's dead, right?
That can't be.
She can't disappear.
Hurry up Hirai,
you don't wanna be late!
What do you say we run for it?
Come on!
What's its deal?
It's worried about its friend
but never thought to
try and save itself.
Finding yourself in
someone else's shoes
can sometimes change
your perspective.
Hirai can't disappear.
I won't let that happen!
Do you know if Ike
has a steady girlfriend?
Ah, Mr. Sakai.
I've warned you
about your tardiness.
Right?
I'm sorry, sir.
'Nother tardy for Sakai.
Um, sir.
What about Hirai?
Oh, thank you.
I didn't see her come in.
Go ahead and
take your seats, you two.
You better watch out;
he'll give you detention.
Yeah.
No one's even looking at Hirai--
it's like she's not here.
Time for lunch, care to join?
I guess so.
What do you say?
Can she join us?
Yeah, I guess so.
Cool?
Hey guess what?
Remember that crazy teacher at
my cram school I told you about?
Turns out he's
Murata's older brother.
That's weird.
Do you have to go back
again after school today?
No, I've got the evening off.
Okay... Then how about
when we got outta school
we head into town and hang out?
Hirai could come with us.
C'mon, you think
you're up for it?
Uh... Sure.
Well, this should be fun.
See? I told you he'd
want to come along.
Move in a little closer, Ike.
Say cheese!
That looks pretty good, huh?
I guess I'm kind of in the way.
I'm sorry about that, Hirai.
Dude, you're being weird.
What do you guys
want to do next?
Try to win a stuffed animal?
Why don't you play a fighting
game against each other?
Hey Ike, can
you entertain Hirai?
I've gotta take
care of something.
Wait a sec.
Sakai!
Quit moving around so much!
I can't keep up!
And just for the record,
no matter how much
you sympathize with it,
it's just a Torch.
You can't stop it
from disappearing.
I know, but I'm trying
to keep everyone
from forgetting about her.
It won't work.
I have to try!
What is with that Torch?
I've never met one so dumb.
Indeed.
Hey, Ike, where's Hirai?
Wha?
Who's this Hirai person?
She was just here
with you a second ago.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah, I know for a fact.
She didn't already
disappear, did she?
Oh, wait.
Now, I remember her--
she must have left already.
Are you sure?
Did she say anything to you?
Don't think so.
Hey! Did I just
beat the whole game?!
I don't care if you
beat the stupid game, Ike--
would you listen to me?
Did she say where she was going?
The three of us were
here, hanging out together,
Hirai was with us!
Do you remember?!
Do you know whether or not
Ike has a steady girlfriend?
What's up?
You've been really
high-strung lately.
What's going on with you?
I shouldn't be mad at him.
This is what happens
to a Torch-- people forget.
He's been acting so weird.
Please Hirai,
don't disappear just yet!
I'm on my way.
Wait for me!
Stupid Torch.
I thought I told it
to stay in one place.
Here you are.
I've been looking for you.
Ike said sorry he had to go but
he has stuff to take care of.
Hey, look.
If you just cut me
out you'll have a
nice picture of the two of you.
Wait.
What did you say?
I've always liked the view here.
It's so pretty.
Yeah, it is.
I see why you
wanted to come here.
Hirai.
What do you say we bring Ike
here with us tomorrow?
That way you can spend
some more time with him,
so you can't disappear
before then, okay?!
Goodbye, Hirai.
Do you understand now?
That is the fate of a Torch.
There's no way to
stop it from happening.
What's left of their flame
will inevitably burn out.
And nobody will remember
that they ever existed.
They disappear without a trace.
You're wrong!
You're wrong.
Because I will remember her!
I know she existed and that
she had a crush on Ike!
Her name was Yukari Hirai!
And I will never forget her.
I swear!
I know she existed.
And so what?
I know that I exist, too.
Whether you recognize it or not,
I know that I am Yuji Sakai.
No, you're nothing but a Torch.
But deep down
I'm still Yuji Sakai.
I exist and so do you!
I am nothing more
than a Flame Haze.
That is all.
In a way,
I'm similar to a Torch.
There has to be more to you
than just being a Flame Haze.
No, I'm afraid there's not.
Because you are just a Torch,
and I'm just a Flame Haze, okay?
That's not true!
It is-- so deal.
It can't be!
What?
What's your name?
Would you please tell
me your name?
I don't have a name,
'cause I'm just a Flame Haze.
You've gotta have a name.
Would you just shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
I don't need a stupid name!
If I need to be distinguished
from other Flame Hazes
for some reason,
then they just call me
'the one with Nietono no Shana'.
Nietono no Shana?
That is the name
of the sword she carries.
Nietono no Shana.
Okay, then your name
is gonna be Shana.
I'll call you that from now on.
Your name is now Shana,
so you're not just
a Flame Haze anymore.
And I'm not just a Torch either.
I'm Yuji Sakai
You can't just give
me a name like that.
Kazumi!
Your bath is ready!
Okay!
I'm going to take those
cookies to Sakai tomorrow.
But I hope he doesn't think I'm
too forward and freak out.
I'll ask Yukari what
she thinks I should do.
Sakai, what's up?
You look weird, dude.
Ike, who's that?
Jeez, dude, what is
with you--that's Hirai.
That's Hirai?
You sure about that?
Hey, Ike!
I need the answers
to last night's homework.
Be right there.
Y'know I'm starting to get
really worried about you, man.
Wanna tell me
what you're doing here?
I already told you.
I have to keep
a close eye on you.
But you didn't have
to follow me to school.
And why are you sitting
in Hirai's seat anyway?
Because I am Yukari Hirai.
I have taken over her existence
therefore I am her now.
What do you mean?
How' do you even do that?
I caught a remnant of
her as she was disappearing.
But you don't
even look like her.
Hi Yukari!
Good morning.
Oh hey, Sakai.
I hope you have
a good morning, too.
Uh.
Same to you.
I did it.
That's crazy.
Yoshida was close friends with
Hirai, and she didn't notice.
Taking over someone's
existence doesn't mean
that I'm trying to
be that person--
in fact, it's the opposite.
I've actually changed
the perspective of others'
so that when they think of
Yukari Hirai they see me.
How could you?
You're a lifesaver, Hirai!
Thanks again for letting
me borrow your notes.
Yep.
This isn't right.
I know who the real Yukari
Hirai is and it's not her.
Good morning, Shana.
It appears the
Flame Haze is keeping
a close watch on that Mystes.
Yes...
She must suspect that
we will come back for it.
And her suspicion
would be correct.
It's only a matter of time.
I guess we should
make an appearance--
I wouldn't want to
disappoint the Flame Haze.
And I'm determined
to get my hands on
the Treasure Tool
within that Mystes.
Please, won't you let me take
care of this for you, Master?
I want to make up
for failing you last time.
If you insist.
Be careful.You mustn't
underestimate the
Flaming Haired-Blazing
Eyed Hunter.
Here, take this with you.
Remember not to wander
too far away from me.
I can do whatever I want.
Hey, Yukari.
So would you like to walk
home together today?
There's something
I wanted to ask you--
I can't.
I've got other plans.
I understand.
I'll leave you alone.
Yukari must be in a bad mood.
She's never snapped
at me like that before.
Be nice, would ya?
Sakai.
Would run over
to the library with me--
I need help carrying some books.
Sure.
They're back.
How do they make
everything freeze like this?
They're using a Seal.
But they can't do that
inside the school, can they?
The location
makes no difference,
all that matters is you're here.
I knew this was going to happen.
You can't fight here!
Someone might get hurt!
I'm afraid we don't
have much of a choice.
I have to fight them.
I don't want my friends
to get dragged into this.
I've gotta keep them safe.
All of this is my fault.
Sorry about this.
Ike!
This'll be easy.
Yoshida, no!
Yoshida!
You're the same Rinne that
I fought against the other day.
What is your Master's name?
You don't honestly
think I would ever tell you.
No, I figured you
weren't gonna tell me.
But I gotta say, he must be a
real idiot since he keeps using
the same silly tactics
over and over again.
I mean come on.
Damn you.
How do you do, young lady?
I was wondering when we'd
finally meet face-to-face.
He must be one of those
Crimson Denizens
Shana was
talking about.
Impressive, I'm
surprised you were able
to defeat my
favorite Treasure Tool.
Regular Sharp usually
poses quite a challenge.
I'm sorry you had
to intervene, Master.
I should be the one
apologizing to you, my dear.
I shouldn't have given you a
Treasure Tool
you've never used before.
That Flame Haze
was so rough with you.
She's a brute, isn't she?
So you're that Rinne's master?
I am.
I am Friagne the Hunter,
and I am Marianne's master.
It's a pleasure to
meet you in person,
Alastor the
Flame of the Heavens.
Don't be fooled by
his appearance,
Friagne is incredibly dangerous.
He has killed
countless Flame Haze
with his many Treasure Tools.
He's an extremely
powerful Crimson Lord.
Got it.
I'm surprised with
your choice of contractor.
The Flaming
Haired-Blazing Eyed Hunter.
I've heard rumor
of your strength
but I have to admit
I'm disappointed.
What did you say to me?
It's a shame, Alastor.
All of your powers
are going to waste.
You never should've entered
a contract with a pathetic
little girl who can't control
the power you've given her.
Give me five minutes and
I'll show you what I can do.
I would love to
but I don't think this is
the right time
for battle, little one.
Besides, I can't chance
harming the Mystes.
But I'll be back.
After all, this is
my hunting ground.
I can't wait to see
what's inside of that Mystes,
but I'll find out, soon enough.
We must be cautious.
He is no ordinary
Crimson Denizen.
Friagne is a Lord
of the Crimson Realm
and known to be a
collector of Treasure Tools.
I'm not surprised
he's after the Mystes.
He mentioned that this
is his "hunting ground."
He must be the reason there are
so many Torches in this city!
Yes, I would venture to guess
that it's all part of his plan.
That guy is insane.
I need to rebuild
before we leave the Seal.
So move,
I need to use that girl.
Use her for what?
I'm going to use what's
left of her power of existence
to rebuild everything
damaged in the battle.
But that would
kill her, wouldn't it?
Well yes, but she's
near death anyway and
since there aren't
any Torches around
I've no choice but to
use the half-dead girl.
What's left of her
power of existence
should be enough
to fix everything.
If you're that worried about her
I can save enough
to make a Torch.
I won't let you!
I don't want Yoshida to go
through what I'm dealing with!
Sorry, but it can't be helped.
I need power of existence to fix
everything back to how it was.
I could just always
use someone else.
What about that guy?
I can't decide.
Well, if you want,
I could just use you.
Let's do that.
Seriously?
You threw a fit when I tried
to use one of them and
then you make a
decision that quickly?
It's the right thing to do.
So you're going to throw away
the little bit of
time you have left?
I'm not throwing it away.
I'm using it!
It's so weird--no, it's
awkward--no, it's annoying!
That Torch is so annoying!
You used a lot of his
existence without hesitation.
What was I supposed to do?!
It told me to use its own
power so that's what I did.
I left it enough to
have a little more time.
I thought I might
find you up here.
What?
I'm not allowed?
No, I didn't say that.
How did you know
where to find us?
It's hard to explain.
I kinda felt you guys up here.
I see.
It makes sense that
after such an intense battle
you would start to
sense our presence.
So what do you want?
Uh, nothing.
I just wanted to
come check on you.
It's weird knowing a girl is
sitting on my roof in the rain.
You should come inside.
Do what?
Well, this can't be comfortable.
Besides, if you wanna keep
an eye on me I would think
you'd probably want
to stay close, right?
Good point.
The thought never
crossed your mind?
It's not some brilliant idea--
there's no need to brag!
What're you talking about?
I wasn't bragging.
Take me inside.
Uh...
Okay, sure.
Follow me.
You can go ahead
and sleep in my bed.
I'll go sleep in my Dad's study.
I came inside so I could
keep watch over you and
now you want to
sleep in a different room?
Uh.
Well, yeah.
You're the one
who thought up this idea.
You'll sleep here.
Whoa!
What do you think you're doing?!
I'm getting undressed.
Isn't that obvious?
Yeah but-It's just--
I should leave.
Why are you embarrassed
all of a sudden?
It's just a Torch,
why do you care?
Go find a place to hide.
Uh, yeah, of course.
Hurry up!
Quit rushing me!
Do you need pajamas?
No peeking!
I wasn't peeking, alright?!
I was just asking if you needed
to borrow some pajamas!
I don't need any.
I can just sleep
in my underwear.
Alastor uses his
flame to purify me so
bathing and changing
aren't really necessary.
So do you really think that
hunter who attacked us at
school is the one who's created
all the Torches in this city?
I'm positive it's him.
I've never seen a
Denizen consume so
much power of
existence in one city.
Although Torches
are used to maintain
the world's balance, it is
also possible to throw off
that balance if there
are too many Torches.
But for all we know,
that could be
exactly what Friagne
is hoping to do.
What good would that do him?
The more Torches
there are in a city the higher
the likelihood that a valuable
Mystes like you will show up.
Which in turn,
lures out Flame Haze.
This city is indeed
his hunting ground.
True, but he's being careless
because he has no way
of being able to know which
Flame Haze is going to show up.
Exactly.
His plan is not without fault.
Although he is a very powerful
Lord of the Crimson Realm.
But I wonder what's giving him
this false sense of confidence.
I'll find out when I
face off with him again.
Since there's no school
tomorrow, maybe you should try
to lure him
outside the city limits.
I'd hate to see more
innocent people get involved.
Good idea.
But that means you're going
to have to come along with us,
since, well you know
you are the bait.
Yeah, I know.
I'll go with you.
That sucked.
I should have punched
him another ten times!
I don't understand
why you're so upset.
It's just a Torch.
You don't get it.
It's no different
than being nude in
front of a rock
or a forest of trees.
Why are you so embarrassed?
You've never cared before.
It just made me
uncomfortable, okay?!
That Torch is like
a human to you.
And you haven't interacted with
a human being in a long time.
Is that it?
I know that it isn't human.
And it's gonna disappear
like every other Torch.
No one will ever be able to
figure out our plan, Marianne.
Not even that pesky
Flame of Heaven.
That may be so, Master,
but I'm worried about
all the Flame Haze that
have come to this city lately.
Please be careful.
Please.
Don't you worry, my dear.
Everything is going
according to plan.
All we need is
a little more power
of existence and we can proceed.
I won't allow them
to hinder our plans.
The Torches light up
the city so brightly.
Once we are victorious our lives
will change for the better.
You won't be just a Rinne
anymore, Marianne.
You will become an existence
that lives within this world.
You're so good to me.
I can't thank you enough for all
you've done for me, Master.
I've just begun,
my dear, Marianne.
It makes me sad.
If I wasn't continually
feeding you energy,
you wouldn't have the
power to last three days.
I don't know what
I'd do if I lost you.
I feel it, too, my love.
I would never want
to be anywhere
but by your side, Master.
Oh!
My sweet Marianne!
Your precious words
have touched my heart.
We'll be together.
I swear to you that I will
make it happen, my love.
That's why we
came to this world.
My sole purpose for seeking
power of existence is for you.
Everything I've done.
It is all for you, Marianne.
Something's not right.
There're too many Torches.
I've never seen so many.
Guess the rumors
we heard were true.
This place really does stink.
Yeah.
It stinks alright.
It smells of your
booze-laden breath!
Shut your trap, stupid Marco!
Oh wow.
You feel that--there must
be another Flame Haze here.
Yeah, I felt it.
Y'know, if someone else
is already on the case
we should probably just drop it.
I don't remember reading
that in the rule books.
I figure whoever gets
there first gets the kill.
At least, that's
how it should work.
Damn straight!
You tell 'em, little lady!
Let's tear this city apart my
beloved goblet, Margery Daw!
Sounds like a plan.
You feel that, Alastor?
Yes.
It's another Flame Haze.
The crew has just
passed the "Yellow Band"
which is about 28,000 feet
above sea level.
We've reached the
part of Mt. Everest
that is considered
the most difficult to climb.
We are currently
prepping to make our
journey to the very
top of the mountain--
I can't do it.
I'm too embarrassed to give
those cookies to
Sakai right now.
I have to build up some courage
and then I'll be able to do it.
Someday I'll be brave enough to
tell him how I feel about him.
Hurry!
I'm coming,
just give me a second.
You're the one who insisted
we fight outside the city.
Did you notice
his flame, Alastor?
It's back to full blaze.
I think I've figured out which
Treasure Tool
is inside that Mystes.
I'm having a hard time
getting used to this.
You know, seeing the Torches.
I feel like I'm invading
their privacy, but it's hard to
avoid looking at
the pulsating flame.
Pulsating?
What do you mean by that?
The flames inside
of the Torches.
They're pulsating
like a heartbeat.
The flame expands and contracts.
Can't you see it?
No, I can't.
Me either.
It's just a steady blue flame.
What?
It's so clear I don't know
how you could miss it.
You're really weird you know.
I've never met
a Mystes like you.
I bet you can see it because of
the Treasure Tool inside of you.
If it is what I think it is,
it's an extremely powerful Tool.
However, there's no
real way of knowing
unless we open you
up and have a look.
It worries me that the Torches'
flames are pulsating.
I've never heard
of such a thing.
Are they all
doing it or just a few?
All of them.
Well, at least
as far as I can see.
A Torch's flame isn't
supposed to pulse like that.
I can't help but
wonder if it's happening
to all of the
Torches in the city.
What do you think it is?
It must be some kind of trick.
An unrestricted spell!
That was a sonar
unrestricted spell.
Hey, why did that
person just disappear?!
In order to
perform such a spell,
someone would need a
lot of power of existence.
I'm assuming that the Torch
was used for that purpose.
Seriously?!
But who would do such a thing?!
Do you think it's
that bastard Friagne?!
No, it's not him.
I suspect it's the Flame Haze
we sensed last night.
I guess they're
not leaving after all.
What?!
There's another Flame Haze
here besides Shana?
Would you just shut up
for one minute?!
It's probably because there
are so many Torches here.
I'm actually surprised that more
Flame Haze haven't noticed.
They must be trying
to lure out the hunter.
Matthew, Mark, Luke and John.
Cover all corners and find the
ghost who disrupts our dreams!
Why are all of the Torches
suddenly disappearing?
It seems that they were somehow
able to figure out my plans.
I'm afraid we're going
to have to hurry, Marianne.
My patience has worn thin;
these visits from
various Flame Haze
have been troublesome.
I shall punish them.
Well, damn it,
I guess he didn't fall for it.
Yeah, but I'll bet
he's hot on our trail.
Who knows?
He could jump out screaming "You
found me!" and try to fight us.
I don't think so, but it seems
we've lured out something else.
What do you think
you're doing here?!
Now, now, what kind
of introduction is that?
Can't I at least get a "hello"?
It's The Claws and
Fangs of Violation
and the Chanter of Elegies!
I should've known
it was you two!
Hey, hey, hey!
How you doin',
old Flame of Heaven?
Let me guess, this is
your Flame Haze, right?
The Flaming-Haired,
Blazing-Eyed Hunter?
Kinda scrawny lookin'.
Why have the
two of you come here?
Are you the one who did it?
Answer me, lady!
What?
You're the one
who did it, right?
How could you?!
How could you
destroy so many Torches
without any kind of remorse?!
Whoa.
Who is this kid?
Evidently he's a Torch as well.
You took their existence,
without even giving
them the chance
to tie up loose ends.
They could have been
trying to help somebody!
You destroyed them.
How could you do that?!
I won't allow you to
talk that way to me, kid.
Maybe you should
destroy that Torch, too!
It's really annoying!
Don't do it!
That Torch is a Mystes.
You mustn't be reckless with it.
Seriously?!
No wonder it got
all bent outta shape.
Damn it.
I'm not trying to side with
the Mystes, however,
I can't fathom destroying
Torches for no reason.
A Flame Haze is
supposed to maintain
the world's balance,
not disrupt it.
What the hell are
you blabbing about?
I think it's more disruptive to
just leave all the Torches here.
I mean, what kind
of balance is that?
Yeah, it's more like the two of
you are neglecting your duty.
We are aware that there
are an excessive number
of Torches here, but it
appears that these Torches
are being used as
part of a larger plan.
What?
Like some kinda trick?
Well, it might be a trap set
by the Flame Haze assassin.
I'm sure you've
heard the horrible news.
Many of our kind have gone
missing after
visiting this place.
That's why we decided to come
out here and check things out.
I'm sure the others
were lured here
by the excessive
number of Torches.
Yeah, we were pretty
shocked when we got here.
There's so many.
It's ridiculous.
Somebody's up to something.
I've got a bad feeling.
Alastor, do you feel it?
I never expected
to stumble upon this.
I thought that Flame Haze
didn't like working together.
It's Friagne!
Well, well, I had a feeling
that we might run into you.
We're up against
Friagne the Hunter!
This is gonna be great!
So, the Chanter of Elegies,
and The Claws and
Fangs of Violation.
Now I know where that crude
unrestricted spell came from.
How could you destroy all the
beautiful artwork I've
created in this city?
You've really pissed me off.
You haven't seen anything yet--
we're just getting started!
Let's do this!
This is it, Friagne!
Your head is mine!
Be careful.
He's dangerous.
You're too slow!
It didn't work!
How'd he avoid it?!
I'm wearing a
flame resistant ring.
It's a Treasure Tool
I acquired called Azure
which allows me to
withstand any flame attack.
I can tell you're a collector.
You're rambling on about some
stupid ring we don't care about.
Yeah, talk about a snooze fest!
I'm sorry to hear that
you're not entertained.
In that case--
I'll step it up a notch.
This one's called Bubble Loot.
And it's one of my favorite
Treasure Tools from
my collection.
There's no weapon
in existence that can
break free from its
golden chains.
I'm done playing your
silly games, Friagne!
Damn it.
I forgot that creep has a
thing for playing with dolls.
If I can't break free,
then I'll destroy the source!
Your dolls can't stop me!
That bell.
Get back!
If we had been any
closer to that explosion
we would've been
goners for sure!
That Mystes sensed it.
It anticipated
the explosion from my
Dance Party Treasure Tool.
I wonder if it's because of
the Tool that's inside of it.
I should dispose of you
for being a nuisance.
Isn't this interesting?
The Flame Haze refuses
to strike the Mystes.
I'll be taking your
little friend with me.
Come back here, coward!
You still want to fight me?
Then I'd be glad to
give you another chance.
If you want to see the
Mystes again then meet
me at the highest point
in the city tonight.
We'll play this out on
the grandest of stages!
I can't believe
we let him get away!
Why didn't you
just slice through it?
I couldn't do it.
These Flame Haze should be easy
for us to defeat,
thanks to that Mystes.
Once we have disposed of them,
the rest should be
a piece of cake my love.
You'll be reborn.
And you will live,
dear Marianne.
You'll become an
existence all your own.
You won't have to rely
on anyone else ever again.
And finally, we'll
be able to be together.
Oh, Master!
So he wasn't just
searching for Treasure Tools.
He was collecting
power of existence
to bring his doll to life!
Damn it. I feel so
helpless just sitting here.
I couldn't do it.
How come?
You've become attached--
it's what happens when
you interact with humans.
But he's not human.
Whoa, don't go overboard!
Why don't you try
sippin' the stuff?!
You're not gonna be able
to fight if you're drunk!
Well, I can't lure him out--
he's not gonna fall for another
sonar unrestricted spell!
So I have no choice but
to sit here and drink
until we meet him at nightfall.
Before we head
into battle tonight,
you should probably
purify me, Marcosias.
Damn it, Margery!
I can't keep using the Purifying
Flame to sober you up!
What have I gotten myself into?
I'm not throwing
it away, I'm using it!
So how long do plan to sit
here feeling sorry for yourself?
I'm having to waste precious
time because of your screw up.
I should be the one who's upset!
Yeah and 'cause of you,
she's hammered!
Look, if you're
not serious about this
then you don't
have to come with us.
I'm coming!
I will fight!
Okay.
There ya go, kid!
Those are the eyes of
the Blazing-Eyed hunter!
I can't wait for tonight!
What d'ya think,
Flame of Heaven?
It's gonna be awesome!
Spectacular, isn't it?
I dare say the perfect stage
for tonight's battle.
All we have to do now is wait
for the Flame Haze to show.
Take a good look, Mystes.
This gun is
called Trigger Happy.
It's a wonderful
little Treasure Tool
that is used to kill Flame Haze.
A Flame Haze uses its body
to contain a Crimson Lord.
In the case of your friend,
that Lord would be Alastor,
one also known as
the Flame of Heaven.
However, a Crimson Lord's power
is hard to keep contained.
For that reason, when
they enter a contract their
existence is put into
a kind of hibernation.
But this gun, my
precious Trigger Happy--
--is capable of liberating the
Crimson Lord from
its containment.
The resulting outpour of
power is absolutely explosive,
and it kills the Lord's
contractor instantaneously.
In other words, the Flame
Haze suffers a fiery death.
Amazing, isn't it?
Furthermore, the freed Lord
is so concerned about
throwing off the
world's balance--
they return to
the Crimson Realm.
I've done this many times--
that's why I've
earned the nickname
the "Flame Haze Assassin."
But for tonight, I chose
a spot high enough that the
Flame of Heaven
wouldn't affect the city below.
Dear Marianne, tonight's
performance is in your honor.
Oh thank you, Master.
I don't get it.
Why is he worried
about affecting the city?
Why would he care if
the entire city was wiped out?
We should get going.
You ready to go on
a rampage, Marcosias?
Hell, yeah! Let's go!
Don't let him shoot you!
He's got Trigger Happy?!
Damn it!
So that's his trump card!
You've got to be careful!
I know.
Silly little girl.
I don't think you're strong
enough to take me on.
Shana!
I thought Flame Haze weren't
supposed to work together.
Well, today is special!
The Torches' pulsing
is getting stronger.
What the hell is going on?
Shana!
He's not just hunting--
he has some sort of plan
set up throughout the city!
What the--
He's pulling power of existence
from Torches all over the city.
That's it!
Friagne the Hunter, are you
attempting a City Devouring?!
You bastard!
A City Devouring?!
There's nothing you
can do about it now.
But yes, I'm performing
a spell that was
cast by a powerful
Crimson Lord long ago.
It allows you to turn an entire
city into pure
power of existence.
You won't be able to stop me.
In fact, it has already begun.
Sorry, you're too late.
If he accomplishes this
City Devouring spell,
everything will be destroyed--
Mom and everyone else will die!
Now that we know what his plans
are it's time to get serious!
C'mon, partner!
Yeah, I know!
But how are we
going to stop him?
We're gonna have to
find a way to kill Friagne!
Hurry! We have to stop him or
the whole world will fall apart!
Right!
What's with the bell?
They don't attack every
time that he rings it. So why?
Now I get it.
The attacks aren't
triggered by the bell!
He's using it to summon
the City Devouring!
I have to tell Shana.
I'm the only one
who has it figured out.
We can still stop it.
We can save the city!
It's up to me to let her know.
All it takes is one
shot from Trigger Happy
and they'll be out of my way.
But these two are
stronger than I expected.
Please, Master Friagne.
Let me take care of them.
No, it's far too dangerous.
Stay here with me.
I have to protect you.
If you were to be killed by
those evil Flame Haze
then I would die along with you.
However, if I died,
you would live on.
Let me do this.
To show my love.
I would gladly give
my life for you, Friagne.
But you are my
reason for living.
Do it now, Master!
Hurry!
My beloved Friagne.
Dear Marianne, as long as I'm
alive, as long as I breathe,
I promise I will work to find
a way to bring you back to life.
And then we'll
be together forever.
Just the two of us.
Just a few more
rings of this bell,
and the City Devouring
will be complete.
But before that, you will die!
Oh crap.
You, will pay for this!
Shana, Seal!
The Seal stopped
the City Devouring.
Destroy it all!
Burn down the
city and everyone in it.
Everything!
Shana!
He shot her!
What the-- ?!
He's been let loose!
The Flame of Heaven.
He's so powerful!
This could be the end of us!
C'mon, we've gotta
hurry up get outta here!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Pick up the pace Marco!
No.
It can't be.
So that's Alastor's true form.
I never thought I'd
see the day that the
Flame of Heaven would be
summoned to this world.
And all because
the scrawny little thing
was shot with Trigger Happy.
Friagne the Hunter.
You are a pathetic fool.
No.
The Flame of Heaven.
Despite your efforts you
have not destroyed the child.
My Flame Haze
is strong enough to
allow me to manifest
and still survive.
She is a miraculous being.
Do you doubt my wisdom
as a Crimson Lord?
I would never enter
a contract with one
who could not handle my power.
This is the end.
Flame of Retribution!
Marianne.
Hey.
So, do you think
I'm gonna make it?
Your flame is very
close to burning out.
I'm afraid it's
nothing more than
a flickering glow right now.
Time's up.
This feels so strange.
I can't believe I'm
actually disappearing,
but you know what,
I'm not sad about it.
I accomplished something.
I may just be a Torch, but I
was able to help save my city.
Even though no one
will ever know about it.
Don't be such a worry wart.
You've done nothing but worry
since the first day we met.
You think so?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Shana.
I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
The name I gave you.
Promise me
you'll continue to use it.
What's going on?!
I'm still here!
I didn't disappear!
But h--?!
How did this happen?!
What's so funny?
You're so silly!
Yuji Sakai, you have
just witnessed the power
of the Treasure Tool
that lies within you.
It fully recovers your power of
existence each day at midnight.
It's called The
Midnight Lost Child.
Then that means--
Yup.
You're not gonna disappear.
The Treasure Tool inside
of you is very valuable
and soon Denizens
will come looking for it.
So we'll continue
to keep watch over you
to make sure
that you remain safe.
That okay with you?
Of course it is.
Glad to hear it.
♪ closing song ♪