I don't think I've been
this far out before.
Oh, really?
You gotta be up early tomorrow?
No I don't.
[MAN] Good, then let's go
a little bit farther.
Th‐there's a spot up ahead
with a beautiful view.
I don't care for this thing.
Yeah well, y'know, you might
wanna go ahead and put it on,
just to be safe.
(chuckles)
Hey, what are you doing?
(gasps)
(tires screeching)
(loud crash)
(pained coughing)
The vital organs are ruined.
My host body will die soon.
I'll use the man.
[MAN] (groans)
[PARASYTE] I see.
The belt does serve a purpose.
[PARASYTE]
(groaning with effort)
My only choice is to relocate
to this man's body.
There should be no difference
in controlling a male host.
Sever the head...
fuse with the host...
and regenerate...
It must all be
done in an instant.
[MAN] (ah...)
[MAN] (huh?)
[MAN] (aahhh!)
[PARASYTE] It feels strange...
I need to move...
C'mon, move...
[SHINICHI] Ah! Oh, crap!
I'm gonna be late!
Why didn't you wake me up?!
[MIGI]
You slept as long as you did
because your body
needed the rest.
If I had woken you up,
I would deprive you of energy.
It's a good thing.
[SHINICHI] Yeah, yeah.
[MIGI]
And of course, your well‐being
is also my well‐being.
Interesting...
it would appear you two
are conjoined.
Ah man, what's that even
s'pos'ta mean?
[MIGI] I'm not certain,
but the reason could lie
in the network of your nerves
and bodily fluids
that are linking my body
to your brain.
Huh?!
It's possible your brain may be
undergoing some kind of change
as well as your body.
Ryoko Tamiya was probably
able to sense it,
and noticed something about you
that seemed inhuman.
She thinks I'm not a human?
The only thing not human
about me's you.
I'm not so sure.
It would not surprise me
if you had changed somehow,
particularly at the
psychological level.
(gasps)
Going to sleep now...
[SHINICHI] Hey, wait a second!
(grrr...)
We're "conjoined"?
Ever so slightly.
I won't be killing you
after all.
No, there's nothing
wrong with me.
Something is just...
Something is different.
You know, Shinichi,
you've changed recently.
I'm not turning into
one of them!
I'm not gonna kill
and eat people.
Huh?
[MAN]
Hey! I thought I said stand up!
(punching sounds)
(ungh!)
[THUG]
You like that, bitch?! Get some!
[NAGAI] (ungh!)
(gasps) Nagai!
(continued punching sounds)
[SHINICHI] Stop it!
[THUGS] (huh?)
[THUG A] You got a problem?
[SHINICHI]
C'mon guys, you need to
leave him alone all right.
(uhhh...) Shinichi?
[GIRL] (giggles) And why's that?
Look, I don't know
what's going on here,
but I thinks he's had enough.
(hmph) Heh...
(ungh!)
Got anything else you
wanna say, Four‐Eyes?
[THUGS] (laughing)
I'm thinkin' the little
shit wants another one.
[GIRL] Just forget it.
It's kinda pitiful.
[GUY] Look pal, we've got some
business with your boyfriend
here, so get lost.
One thing I don't understand
about the human psyche
is the notion of
"self‐sacrifice."
Doing something to
assist another being,
at a cost to oneself,
is unnatural.
I do no see the benefit
in this at all.
[SHINICHI] The human psyche...
[THUG] C'mon, get up, asshole.
[NAGAI] (groans)
[THUG]
We're just gettin' started.
[SHINICHI] That's it!
[THUG] Hope you got some time!
Human beings are different
from parasites!
Hey! I said to stop it!
(kicking &amp; punching)
[SHINICHI]
It's not much of a fight
[THUGS] (huh?)
when you have someone
outnumbered!
[GIRL] (huh?)
Yo, dude...
You sure you wanna do this? Hmm?
Yeah, I do.
[GUY] (heh)
[SHINICHI] Might've been a bad
idea... (ungh!)
(punching sounds)
[GUY]
This it? This what you wanted?
Don't you think you're
overdoing it a little?
[SHINICHI] (ungh)
[GUY] Not yet.
You heard the dumbass,
he was askin' for it right?
[GUY] (gahn)
[SHINICHI] (ungh)
Oh, no, Migi's not gonna know
what this is about!
All right that's enough!
It's kinda lame to pick on
someone so weak and sad.
[GUY] Must be your lucky day.
Mind your own business.
It's less painful. (gasps)
Ah!
(gasps)
Wha...
What... What are you?
[GUY]
Come on, let's get outta here.
Hey there, Nagai,
you doing okay?
Jesus Christ, man, you crazy?
Maybe... That was probably
pretty stupid, huh?
But hey, that's the kinda stuff
that separates us from the
animals, right?
Hmm?
(bell chiming)
[SATOMI] Oh, my God,
what happened to you?
Don't worry, it's nothing.
I'm okay.
[YUKO] I asked him that, too.
And he wouldn't tell me either.
D'you get in a fight, or, uh...
[KAMIJO] Hey, Shinichi.
[All] (huh?)
Nagai just got through
tellin' me.
He said you took on
Mitsuo's whole crew.
I wouldn't say I took them on.
They killed me. Look at my face.
Those guys have been doing
more and more crap
like that lately.
If they try anything else,
you let me know, okay?
Oh, sure.
Uh... It's you!
So I guess you have
a girlfriend?
[SHINICHI] What do you want?
Why didn't you
run away earlier?
[SHINICHI]
Huh? I just couldn't...
You barely even know that guy
and stood up for him,
and you got your ass kicked.
This guy's not quite
right is he?
Do what?
What's that supposed to mean?
[SHINICHI] Let's go.
I can see through you!
You can pretend to be
all self‐righteous,
but I know that
you're up to something!
[SATOMI] What's her deal?
[SHINICHI] I dunno.
Dammit, Kana...
(loud crash)
[SATOMI] (ah!) Stop it!
[SHINICHI] (ungh!)
[SATOMI] (screams)
(pained groans)
[SATOMI] (whimpers)
Shinichi, help!
Murano!
Shinichi!
There you are, you piece‐a‐shit.
[SHINICHI]
Just let her go! Come on!
[GUY] Nah, I don't think so.
Go on home;
we'll take care of her.
[SHINICHI] What?
[SATOMI]
(whimpers) Ow, that hurts!
[THUG] That's right!
(grrr...)
(ungh!) (argh)
Shinichi, no!
I said go!
[SATOMI] Please, stop it!
Y'ain't actin' like
a frickin' hero this time!
Face it, you can't do
a goddamn thing.
(panting)
[MIGI] Shinichi...
No not now, Migi.
You can go back to sleep.
[MIGI] Shinichi...
[SHINICHI]
I can take care of this.
[SHINICHI] (hyah)
(ungh)
[MIGI]
For your reference, I will rate
each of them by strength.
If your rating is a ten,
then he's an 18.
The one to the right is a 13,
and the others are 14 and 12.
Migi, why are you
telling me all this?
[MIGI] Even dogs and cats
are able to evaluate
the strengths and weaknesses
of their opponents.
Animals instinctively avoid
fights they cannot win.
[SHINICHI]
Yeah, so what's your point?
[SHINICHI] (ungh!) (urggh)
[SATOMI] Leave him alone!
Well, sometimes a human
can't back down from a fight.
There's a difference between
humans and animals.
Migi, I don't have much
feeling in my hand!
Give me full control! (ungh!)
Sorry, you got something to say,
you'll have'ta speak up!
(coughing &amp; gasping)
Man, why doesn't he
just give up?
[SHINICHI]
You are gonna let her go!
Or else!
(gasps)
Wait! No, Migi, stay outta this!
(huh?)
[GUY] "Or else," what?
You'll run home and
tell your mommy?
[THUGS] (derisvie laughter)
I, uh, think that's enough,
Mitsuo.
[MITSUO] Kana...
[KAMIJO] Well, well,
look what we have here.
[ALL] (huh?)
[SHINICHI] Kamijo, Nagai!
[MIGI] Ah, yes, the majority
overpowering the minority.
These humans actually make
much more sense than you do,
Shinichi.
Looks like it's time for some
payback, you son of a bitch.
You think cause you brought some
friends you've got a chance?
You've made a big mistake.
SHUT UP!
(melee sounds)
(waves crashing)
Hmm... The male genitalia
are actually quite different
from the female.
I can't seem to control them
very well. (grunt)
Something's wrong, I can't move.
Damn! It's rejecting me!
I can no longer merge with
a body of the opposite sex.
I must find a woman.
Leaving the urban area
was a mistake.
I must find a new host
and relocate.
[SHINICHI] Look, it's not like
I can't walk or anything.
I'm fine, really.
Uh, no, you're not.
[SATOMI] I'm really sorry.
There's nothing that
you need to apologize for.
Oww, ow!
Oh, huh? Your right hand
isn't even scratched.
Cause I mean, your left hand
sure got messed up pretty badly.
[SHINICHI] (ah... uh...)
Ah... How 'bout that?
Tell me...
Do you think that I'm weird?
[SATOMI] (huh?)
Do I seem normal to you?
Oh, no, you are not
normal at all.
I'm not?
Well, you're kinda cool
[SHINICHI] (huh!) (embarrassed)
You risked yourself
to help a friend.
Not many "normal" people
out there would do that.
Is that s'posta be a compliment?
[SATOMI] Of course.
[SHINICHI] (ah!)
I've never known anyone who
would try something like that,
knowing you couldn't win.
You did a really good thing.
[SHINICHI] Oh, okay.
My parents are out of town
right now...
Do you maybe wanna stay over?
Mmm... No, thanks...
I should go.
(small giggle)
[MIGI] Very disappointing.
I'd hoped I'd get the chance
to see humans mate.
Oh, go to sleep.
[KANA] Who are you talking to?
You followed me home?
[KANA] I just came to apologize.
Oh, uh...
Okay, then.
A truce?
[SHINICHI] (hmm?)
Well, at the very least,
WE don't have a problem, do we?
Um...
Yeah...
(gasps)
(uh!) S‐sorry,
I'm really... tired.
[MIGI] You should be careful
when it comes to that female.
It seems she is able to sense,
however slightly,
wavelengths that should only be
perceptible to parasites.
But she is human, right?
I've noticed Murano's also a
very perceptive person.
But THIS girl is on
a whole different level.
You should stay away from her.
[SHINICHI] Yeah...
(waves crashing)
[MOM] Wow, this is beautiful!
Yeah, kinda makes all that
rushin' around to get here
worthwhile doesn't it?
We should come back here.
(giggles)
And bring Shinichi with us!
(chuckles) He's never far
from your mind, is he?
(huh?!) Nobuko!
[MOM] (huh?)
(hissing) (thwack)
(sighs)
[MIGI] Your diet appears
to be unbalanced.
You don't even know what
this tastes like.
[MIGI] Your mother always
prepares nutritionally
appropriate meals.
Well, I can eat like that
again tomorrow.
(phone buzzes)
It's from a public phone.
[DAD] Shinichi?
[SHINICHI] Yeah, Dad?
[DAD] Y‐your mother...
Uh... what's wrong?
[DAD] Your... your mom...
I'm going to the police.
I'll get that damned monster
if it's the last thing I do!
(unnhhh...) (loud thump)
Wait, Dad?! A monster?!
(dead line)
[SHINICHI]
"A monster"? It can't be...
But... but Mom...
[MIGI] Shinichi, what is it?
[SHINICHI] Dad! Mom!
What's going on?
What is this place?
[DAD] We're in no rush.
We'll just decide where to stop
as we go along.
[MOM] It'll be nice to just
relax and take it easy.
[SHINICHI] Dad, where's Mom?
[DAD] That goddamn monster!
[SHINICHI] She's not a monster,
she's... Mom! (echoing)
[MOM] Shinichi...
[SHINICHI] MOM! (echoing)
(gasps)
Come on, Dad,
you gotta call me back.
I gotta figure out
a way to find them!
Shinichi, you really need
to get some sleep.
"A monster..."
That's exactly what
Dad said on the phone.
I know that can
only mean one thing.
Hmm... Hold on, Shinichi.
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
I'm detecting
one of my kind nearby.
And it's coming
directly toward us.
This is all your fault.
I was against them taking the
trip in the first place.
But you said they'd be safe;
you said it would be fine!
I never said that
it would be "fine."
I merely pointed out that,
in terms of probability‐
Shut up! I should've told them
about what was really going on
when you showed up
in the first place!
I understand there's a lot
you'd like to discuss right now,
but I need you to focus on the
battle that's about to commence.
No, you won't need
a weapon this time.
I will eliminate it before
it's able to determine
whether or not
we are friend or foe.
I can't face this thing unarmed.
I'm so full of hate right now,
I'm going crazy.
Those damn monsters!
[MIGI] It stopped moving...
It's just outside.
(lock clicking)
How could it unlock the door?
(footsteps)
(ah!) It's you!
[SHINICHI] Mom?
So, then the male
has not yet returned.
What's that Mom?
That's not your mother.
You know that.
Uh, welcome back!
Mom, are you doing okay?...
What's the matter?
[MOM]
This is a unique situation.
A merge with the hand
is highly unusual.
One of my kind has taken over
your mother's head, Shinichi.
Huh? My hand?
Yeah, I'm so sorry, Mom.
I mean, I really wanted to tell
you about it earlier, but I...
I just couldn't. I, uh...
I mean, it's kinda crazy, right?
No, Shinichi, she's not‐
[SHINICHI] JUST SHUT UP!!
Am I to assume
the male is now dead?
I see.
Then I must go back and confirm
whether or not he's
actually been eliminated.
The knife, it's in my way.
Put it down.
So, yeah, I know, having a
talking right hand is
pretty weird.
I mean hard to believe right?
Just the hand? How unlucky.
Without taking the head,
you find yourself under
human control.
(grr...) Stop it, Mom!
I'll tell you everything
I've been hiding from you!
Just, please,
stop talking like that!
Shinichi, you have to see
what's happening.
Your mother is already‐
Shut up! JUST SHUT UP!
You don't know what
you're talking about!
If you keep talking,
[MIGI] Shinichi!
I swear I'll cut you off!
(breathing heavily)
Please, Mom!
It's okay...
You remember it right?
The scar on your arm?
Every time I see it,
I feel guilty.
And, Mom, I...
I wanna apologize.
(gasps)
Shinichi!
(unhhh...)
(unhhh...) (sobs)
Mom...
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"The Sun Also Rises"