Uh? Ah...
Uh...
[NOBUKO]
I have punctured
the boy's heart...
Your human host
is now dead.
And you will follow
in a matter of minutes.
Now you must accept your fate
as one who was unsuccessful
in seizing the head.
[MIGI]
There's no time to waste.
A direct hit to the heart
is critical and cannot be
repaired very quickly.
At this rate, Shinichi's
brain will soon be
rendered inoperable...
My only available option
is to merge myself...
with his heart.
As I am sealing the wound,
I must initiate heart function
while also circulating
the blood within myself.
The parasite we just encountered
seems to have successfully
relocated to another
host's head,
but this is a far
riskier venture.
[Heart beating]
Ah...
[Coughing]
[Labored breathing]
[MIGI]
Good. It seems this
might actually work.
But I can't expect an
instantaneous recovery.
I'll slowly gather cells from
throughout his body to aid
in the healing process.
In the meantime,
I will begin to gradually
return to his right hand
through his bloodstream...
[SATOMI]
Huh? Shinichi's absent
again today?
Yeah... I heard the
teacher tried calling
his house a few times,
but no one answered.
I'm really worried.
Wanna swing by
there later?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, but we don't know
where he lives...
I do...
I sorta went home with him
after school the other day.
Huh?!
[AKIHO]
Hey, Murano!
I didn't know you and
Shinichi were a thing.
Is it serious?
What?! No!
I mean we're not a thing.
Oh yeah, excuse me.
You just went home with him
"casually"... Hehe...
Akiho, this is none
of your business.
Quit being so nosey,
get your own life alright.
C'mon, I want all
the juicy details!
[AKIHO]
What'd you do at his house?
Did you see his bedroom?
So are Shinichi and Murano...
Was it clean or nasty?
really dating?
Did you make out or what?
I don't know.
Who cares!
[AKIHO]
C'mon, girl spill it!
Gimme some dirt!
[SATOMI] Could you just drop it!
[YUKO] Seriously.
Sugar.
[Faucet squeaks]
[Water running]
[Breathing]
[Drinking]
[Phone rings]
Unhh...
[Struggling]
Uhh...
Hmm...
Huh?!
Hm...
[Coughing, vomiting, sighing]
[Panting]
[SHINICHI]
The wound... It's sealed...
But it looks like it's been
fused together or something.
Migi?
Did Migi heal me?
[Whimper]
Ahh...
It wasn't...
It wasn't a dream?!
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Ah, I'm glad we
finally got you!
I'm calling from
Sakurazaki Hospital.
Have I reached Mr. Kazuyuki
Izumi's residence?
Yes...
Ah! My Dad!
That's my Dad!
Oh, don't worry.
He's fine.
[Sirens outside]
He's getting some rest
at the moment,
but he's in stable condition,
and he's not in any danger.
I just wanted to suggest,
when you come to visit,
if you could bring him
a change of clothes
and maybe some‐
[SHINICHI] I'll be right there!
Oh...!
Shinichi?
[Closes door and locks it]
Um... You haven't been
to school lately,
so I came to check on you.
You mentioned that your
parents were on vacation,
so I was worried that maybe
you had gotten sick,
and you were just laid up
here all by yourself...
Uh...
Found out my dad was
in an accident while
they were away.
Oh?!
Wow... your mom must really
be struggling right now.
Uhh...
Oh!
[Gasp]
Look... I won't be back
at school for a while.
Uh...
Shinichi...
Shinichi!
You... you will...
come back, right?
[SHINICHI]
I'll kill it!
That thing is dead!
It was able to get away...
but not before Dad had
the chance to see
what that monster
really looks like...
in its true form.
So then the male...
has not yet returned?
But how did it
find our address?
From their luggage...
or at their hotel?
I'm sure it won't be long
before that thing figures out
which hospital Dad's in.
I don't have much time...
I have to hurry!
[Girl]
Um... um, excuse me!
Hm?
Are you doing okay?
You uh, you look like you're
kinda worried or something,
so I thought I'd see
if you're alright.
[SHINICHI]
Are you from Sakurazaki?
Yeah. I am.
So, do you know
Sakurazaki Hospital?
Oh! Yes.
I know where that is.
[DETECTIVE]
So, Mr. Izumi,
it was the night of
the 18th, correct?
That's when you say
your wife was killed.
Yes.
Has she...
Has my wife's body been
found yet, Detective?
Mr. Izumi...
Hmm?
I believe your wife
is very much alive.
Huh?
[DETECTIVE 2]
On the 18th...
that's the day on which you
reportedly struck your head
and fell into the ocean...
Your wife returned to the
hotel alone about 9:00 pm.
That's impossible!
We did confirm...
The staff at hotel's front desk
said they spoke with her.
[Confused groan]
She told them you had to
leave on urgent business,
but that she would stay on
for one more night.
She then checked out
the following morning.
No...
That can't be right!
It had to be somebody else!
Um sir, the hotel
staff confirmed
the burn mark located on
the woman's right forearm.
They've stated that they're
certain she was the same
person who arrived with you.
[Trembling]
Mr. Izumi...
In my opinion, I believe
that the terrible shock
you've suffered
is causing you to confuse
reality from before your
traumatic accident
with perhaps a nightmare
you had afterwards.
No way...
That was not a dream!
[Heart beat]
I know what I saw!
Ugh... Uh...
[Girl running]
This is it.
[SHINICHI]
Thank you so much.
Hehe... See ya!
Yes. He's right
down there.
[Shinichi running]
Huh?
Dad, I'm here!
Shinichi.
Dad... I uh...
I'm sorry that I made
you worry, Son.
Dad...
But Mom... she's...
Uh, I can't handle this...
It hurts so much
I can barely talk...
and... and I can't even cry.
Shinichi, what's wrong?
[Heavy breathing]
It's Mom, Dad she's...
Shinichi... About that...
It seems that something has
happened to your mother...
and well, we don't know
where she is.
Huh?
But, Dad...
You saw it!
Saw what?
What do you mean?
Well... The doctor says
that I'm confused...
Like, looks like I hit
my head pretty hard, Son.
But Dad... No...
I've asked the police to keep up
their search for her...
The doctor wants me to stay
here for a while longer,
but it's nothing serious.
So please don't worry.
[SHINICHI]
"Don't worry"?
How can you even say that?!
Shinichi, did something
happen back home?
What? Well of course
something happened!
Mom has been murdered
by some monster!
Dad, you know that!
Is that what I told you?
I told you all that nonsense...
on the phone?
Ugh... I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry! I was losing it!
What? Does he really think
it's all in his head?
Son, I'm going to recover
and be just fine.
I want you to try and
take it easy for a few days,
and go back home.
I know it's tough, but hang in
there just a little bit longer.
If you have any problems,
then you can always go
to your uncle's house‐
Dad. I need to
tell you something.
Hmm?
It's about Mom
and the monster‐
Shinichi!
Uh...
Please. Not right now...
Dad...
He's crying...
He knows, doesn't he?
He knows that Mom is dead.
I want to tell him the truth
about what that
monster really is...
About the creature
that killed her.
If only Migi...
If only Migi was actually
an ally of humanity.
Here, I brought
you some clothes.
So where are you going
to stay, Shinichi?
Here with you.
C'mon you know you can't get
a good night's rest in here.
They told me about a hotel
that's right by the beach.
That's where you
should be staying.
I'm at a hospital...
and Migi's asleep...
This could be my chance
to get him looked at!
No, now's not the time.
I need his abilities to find
the enemy.
And fight them.
I hate to admit it, but...
I have no choice but to
trust Migi and rely on him.
Huh?!
The Sakurazaki Hotel,
is that far away
from here?
Um, no, not far at all.
In fact, it's just a few
blocks away from here.
A few blocks...
That's at the edge of Migi's
ability to detect our enemies.
If that thing shows up
at the hospital,
we might not be able
to make it in time.
This is perfect.
Right behind the hospital.
Hello, excuse me.
[Footsteps]
Uh...
I guess, you'll be
needing a room?
[SHINICHI]
It's you!
Hehe...
Hey, Mom! We have a
guest checking in!
Dad must've seen it...
He saw Mom get killed.
At some point,
I'm going to have to tell him
everything I know.
But for now...
I just have to keep him alive...
and avenge Mom's death.
[Footsteps]
Excuse me... your dinner's
ready for you downstairs.
Get it while it's hot!
[SHINICHI]
Thanks.
Hm‐hm.
I could totally tell
that she was coming.
Are the walls that thin,
or has my hearing
somehow improved?
[MIGI]
Shinichi.
I thought I might
keep this to myself,
but I've decided to tell you.
It's very important.
The feelings you have
for your family are
incredibly strong...
However, your feelings
for me are practically
nonexistent...
Actually, I know you
think of me as more of
a hinderance at best.
And while we do act as allies,
one could say that
we are really enemies
forced into a
difficult situation.
Yeah, so what's
your point?
You see, during the time
that I was repairing
your damaged body,
it would seem that my body
underwent a change as well.
A change?
That's correct.
I have now developed a weakness
that others of my kind have
never experienced.
Every day now,
for about four hours,
I fall completely and
totally asleep.
That's it? But you've
always gone to sleep.
Not like this...
Previously, even the
slightest disturbance
would awaken me immediately.
For instance,
if you were surprised,
or if your breathing was uneven.
Or if...
one of my associates
approached within 300 meters.
"Associates"?
Correct...
But since this change
has occurred,
it appears that while asleep,
I am able to detect nothing.
So, if an enemy were
to appear during that
four‐hour sleep cycle...
it would mean...
the end for both of us.
Oh...
Repairing your heart
meant that I had to spend
an extended period of time
detached from your arm.
And as a result, my physiology
has been slightly altered.
Why would you wait so long
to tell me about this?!
Well, ever since one
of my fellow parasites
killed your mother,
you have been harboring a great
deal of hostility toward me.
You must realize that revealing
one's weakness to an enemy
is extremely dangerous,
so that's why I said
nothing until now.
However, I determined that
if you weren't made aware
of this problem...
the situation would become even
more dangerous for us both...
Do you understand?
Yes, I do...
But I don't really
think of you
as an enemy
anymore, Migi.
You did save
my life, you know.
That's not entirely
accurate, of course...
Since there was my life
to consider as well.
[MAKIKO]
Morning!
Oh... good morning.
Oh, hey... There's more
color in your cheeks...
Yesterday you were looking
kinda ragged, ya' know.
Hmm...
So I guess you
slept well, then.
Hehe...
[IZUMI]
Oh, thanks.
It's been a while since you were
able to read the paper, huh?
It has. When I fell
into the water...
my tablet and my cell phone
were both completely destroyed.
Then we'll have to get
you new ones when
you get home.
Uh‐huh...
When're you uh...?
I'm gonna stay a bit longer
and see how things go, okay?
Whenever Migi is
in a deep sleep...
I'll have to use my
own eyes to keep watch.
I'll try to have Migi
sleep during the day
if that's possible,
when people are around
and there's less chance
of an attack.
Now, if that thing
does show up here,
how would it approach?
Migi told me not to fight
unless he was awake...
but I may not be
given a choice.
I'll have to defend
myself somehow.
Besides, I am not going to
run from my mother's killer!
[MAKIKO]
Hello there!
Uh...
Hey, uh...
It's...
It's Makiko, isn't it?
You can call me Maki.
Have you been sitting
out here all this time?
I guess you must be really
worried about your father, huh?
Um... Well, yeah...
And I don't really
have much else to do.
Ah...
Um, do you have
a girlfriend?
Huh?
[MIGI]
Shinichi. I sense one.
Huh...
It's just about
300 meters away,
in the direction
of the beach.
It's here!
Hey Maki, which way is it
to get to the beach?
Huh?
If you head straight
down the road
back to my place and‐
Huh...
Wait, hold on!
If you just go straight,
you'll hit the seawall!
Stop!
Hold on!
[Panting]
Hey!
He's so fast!
[MIGHI]
Shinichi.
I need to confirm.
[SHINICHI]
Yeah, what?!
Is it all right
to kill her?
[Heavy breathing]
Yes! Something like that
cannot be allowed to
roam free in this world...
I cannot allow it!
[Makiko panting]
Ahh...
You just took off
before I got the chance
to finish telling you
exactly how to get there.
To get down to the beach,
you're gonna have to circle
around the west side‐
Huh?
Whoa!
Huh? I just saw it
down at the far end
of the bridge.
This is it!
Shinichi, I have
something else
I need to tell you.
And it's something
about you.
It has finally become clear
to me that you have‐
Just save it!
You're not getting away!
You will pay...
for what you did to my mother!
[Grunt]
You're dead!
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"A Dark Night's Passing"