Ah, hello.
[RADIO] Yayoi Squad
has engaged Hirokawa.
Do not let him get away.
Make sure he's taken out.
Welcome, gentlemen,
so nice of you to come.
It is certainly an honor
to have you all here.
When it comes to
the art of death,
every species on Earth pales
in comparison to that of
the human race.
Yet, as I look at the
fine instruments you hold,
I feel they could be put to
a FAR greater purpose.
Such implements of force can be
used NOT for simple eradication,
but rather the protection of the
balance of our very existence.
That's right: to purge those
who offer NOTHING to
our community.
Because when put to task,
all of us must admit
an obvious truth:
that not everyone in our vast
population deserves to be
part of our family.
Instead, they attack our values.
They attack our ecosystem,
in a crime of arrogant apathy
far greater than that
of crude genocide.
Yet, hope is here.
It's staring you in the face.
It may be different
and seem frightening,
but you will come to cherish it.
The time has come that we must
hold our own predators
in high regard,
and in fact protect them.
And the most fascinating thing,
is that these predators will
ultimately allow us to grow
stronger and more powerful.
They are our saviors,
our masters.
(on speaker)
And they will restore the
balance that we could not.
Hirokawa...
Not long ago, someone on Earth
had a passing thought:
"All life is sacred and must
therefore be protected."
[SOLDIER] Who do you think
you are, you monster?!
[HIROKAWA] (hmph) This is why
I cannot abide my own kind.
If defiance is truly
your intention,
do not pretend
and act otherwise.
Even environmental conservation
is skewed in favor of
our own hubris,
a viewpoint most
refuse to acknowledge!
We MUST consider
all life on Earth,
not just the prosperity
of a single species!
THAT presumes your own
rule over creation!
Humans repeatedly claim
they're on the side of justice,
and what greater justice is
there than natural selection?!
The human race has
been inhabited,
and relinquished of the
sacred duty
by preserving the balance
of life on Earth!
Thus, exposing YOU as nothing
but parasites infesting
this planet!
It's you...
You are the infection!
We're the... infection?
[RADIO] Fire!
(multiple gunshots)
(urk!)
(ungh...)
(thump!)
(running steps)
(nervous breaths)
[SOLDIER 2] What's wrong?
[SOLDIER] The mayor was a human.
[SOLDIER 2] He what?!
(loud crash)
[BOTH] (huh?!)
Hirokawa, huh?
Right up to the end, I never did
quite understand him.
Reiko Tamura was
especially intrigued by him,
and had several
initiatives underway.
But that's all over now.
(chuckles)
This must be rather upsetting...
a human like this among you.
[KATSUMATA] (waaahhh!)
No... no... I don't...
Wh‐what the hell is this?
What happened here?!
[URAGAMI] I'm tellin' ya,
this was that guy from before.
He's more powerful
than the others are.
I mean you can't even shoot him.
Report.
[RADIO] Hirokawa has been
neutralized, but...
Well, another parasite
has arrived.
(gunfire)
[YAMAGISHI] (huh?!)
We'll meet Minazuki Squad
and head over there.
We're on our way now.
(single gun shot)
(uhhh...) U‐Uragami...
You bastard!
Oh man, my hand's all numb.
Guess that's why knives've
always been my thing.
Say "cheese."
(gun shot)
(ungh...)
Holy shit!
It blew his whole hand off!
You had to know this would
happen, Detective.
I mean, I was already
on death row.
I've got nothing to lose.
(loud clatter)
Now to get outta here.
That big guy is so powerful
he'll break through eventually,
and that's MY chance.
[GOTO] Reiko Tamura would often
question our purpose here,
and wonder why we were born.
I guess...
none of that matters anymore.
The reason for my existence
is to fight.
[MIGI] Shinichi, let's go home.
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
There's no point in us
staying any longer.
After all, our work here
is finished now.
(whispering) How can you be
so sure about that?
And besides, we really have
to see if that Goto guy
can be taken down.
[MIGI] It doesn't matter.
The humans have already won.
If they really wanted to,
they could use cannons or
missiles or even bombs.
They can do whatever they want.
At this stage, we, as
individuals, no longer have
any say in what happens.
(huh?)
You're acting strange, Migi.
(naked footsteps approaching)
[SOLDIER] Fire!
(multiple gun shots)
(smashes door)
[YAMAGISHI]
How can he move like that?
(ahhh!)
[GOTO]
You can do better than that.
Humans are supposed to be the
most intelligent life forms
on the planet.
Isn't that right?
(gun shots)
[SOLDIER] He can dodge gunfire?!
(urk!) (ungh!)
I can do more than that.
[SOLDIERS] (groaning)
I'm improving all the time.
Please, please don't shoot me!
Open fire.
They're beyond our help.
[SOLDIER] No, don't!
(multiple gun shots)
If this monster is
able to move like this,
then that drastically limits
our firing options indoors.
We're at too great a risk
of shooting our own men.
We need a more open area.
Let's fall back!
To the roof.
Let's go, now!
(grrr...)
(large explosion)
One more round.
[SOLDIER] But shouldn't
that have finished him?
Stay vigilant.
We need to be twice as cautious,
and engage him on our terms.
[YAMAGISHI] This guy's
comfortable using the
walls, floor, and ceiling.
Standard indoor combat tactics
are useless here.
This place is his lair,
and we're inside it!
It's sad to think we humans
lost our advantage
in a structure we created.
(boom!)
[YAMAGISHI] All right,
split up left and right!
We'll take him out here!
(gasps)
[GOTO] What talk is this?
(door squeaking)
Son of a bitch...
You're all alone, Captain.
You don't have any more men
left to help you out.
Although, I should say...
They wouldn't've helped anyway.
(wind blowing)
That body of yours seems
to be rather special.
It's like it's armored!
That's correct.
But it doesn't protect
my entire body, unfortunately.
There are gaps.
Through sheer firepower,
you actually got the better
of me to some extent.
(grrr...)
(gun shots)
Even if I harden my cells,
deflecting gunshots head‐on
is still a risky proposition,
which is why I deflect
them at an angle.
Godammit!
Don't toy with me!
(large explosion)
(smug chuckle) (gasps)
Although I am able
to dodge gunfire,
it's not that I actually
move faster than a bullet.
I just predict its trajectory
based on my opponents' eye
and hand movements.
[YAMAGISHI] (oofff!)
[POLICE] Did you hear that?
[POLICE 2]
I think it came from the roof.
(gurgling cough)
[YAMAGISHI]
What the hell are you, anyway?
As you can clearly see, I am
simply a pure, feral life form.
[YAMAGISHI]
You're... an abomination.
And what are humans exactly?
Go to Hell.
(weak chuckle)
Oh a flamethrower, huh?
That might've been a good idea,
kid.
[SHINICHI] (ahhh...)
(loud clang) (bushes rustling)
See that?
Something fell from up there.
[POLICE] (WAAAHHH!)
(ugh!) Hey, what was that for?
[MIGI]
I told you we should leave.
[GOTO] Well, well, it's you.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
(waaah...) Ah, Goto!
[GOTO] I see...
So you were involved
with this attack, too.
And it was a rather
intense battle at that.
In fact, it seems that
all others of my kind
were destroyed.
And if you were a part
of this operation,
there's still some
unfinished business here.
I'm sure killing you
will be most satisfying.
And besides,
I believe I need to kill you.
And when it's done,
I will move forward.
"Move forward"?
(rapid gun shots)
Your aim was actually
quite accurate,
if you intended to
target the heart.
What in the hell?
But this fight must wait.
There are too many others,
and I'm feeling a
bit tired today anyway.
[HIRAMA] He... he just flew!
Shinichi Izumi,
what have you done?
Huh?! I didn't do anything!
I didn't! I swear!
[HIRAMA] Wait right there!
A lot of men died,
well trained men...
men under Yamagishi's command.
You saw it.
All it took was one monster,
and it was able to overtake us.
You expect me to believe
you knew nothing?
You're doing it again.
You're hiding something, dammit!
No, I'm not!
I honestly had no idea
that just one of these things
could do something like this!
[POLICE] A head!
Someone's head
fell off the roof!
Hey, Shinichi.
[SHINICHI] (waaah!)
(panicked breathing)
[MIGI] Shinichi,
that was a terrible dream.
(deep breath)
Migi, how do you know
what I dreamed about?
I just do somehow.
Will Goto be coming after us?
He most definitely will,
and it'll be soon.
I could sense how strong
his resolve was.
[SHINICHI]
So... We're going to die.
[MIGI] No, we can't
give up that easily.
We should try to
go get some help.
Like Uda, for example.
[SHINICHI] Forget it.
We can't drag
those two into this.
Well, we can get
the humans to help.
They can deploy the military
against him again.
How can we do that?!
And even if we did,
countless more people will die!
And we'd be responsible
for their deaths!
Why should I care?
(chuckles)
Migi...
You never really do change,
do you?
[SHINICHI] Dad...
I'm afraid I might be
saying goodbye soon.
And Mom...
I might be
seeing you again soon.
[SHINICHI] I got it.
Why don't we just
run somewhere far away?
I mean he's not...
He can't be so obsessed
he'd track us across
the country right?
Hey, Migi, are you asleep?
Ah! I forgot to go
to school today.
(laughs) ...school!
(huh?)
Are you asleep?!
Migi!
(gasps)
(waaah!)
(huh?)
(panicked running)
[SHINICHI] If he shows up now...
(whimpering)
If he... if he shows up now...
(ugh)
Hey!
You gonna apologize, asshole.
I... I'm sorry.
He's totally scared, dude!
Get down on your knees.
Please forgive me.
I am so sorry.
[PUNK] That's a good boy.
(WAAAHHH!)
(ungh!)
[PUNK 2] No, no! (ugh!)
I apologized, didn't I?!
You got what you wanted, huh?!
I said it! I said it!
Are you happy now?!
(gasps)
[SATOMI] Shinichi?
Um, hey there.
(uh...)
Ah, so did you really
skip school again today?
Uh‐huh.
I sure did.
Just the kind of guy I am,
ya know?
I'm a scumbag.
Uh, what was that?
You're acting weird.
(soft chuckle)
(half‐sobs)
Wha...
[SHINICHI] (whimpering)
Stop that! It hurts!
Please, let go.
Stop it!
[BOTH] (heavy breathing)
(grrr...)
[SATOMI] (ah!) Shinichi?!
(dog barking)
[MIGI] Your idea to run far away
may not be a bad one, Shinichi.
Oh, hey.
Guess you were awake then, huh?
Just run away... Yeah...
And right when I'm finally
so close to graduating.
(chuckle)
[MIGI] Shinichi...
Your senses seem to be
a little dull at the moment.
(huh?!)
Well, hello there.
[SHINICHI] How did you know
you could find me here?
(sighs)
[SATOMI] You really like
this park, don't you?
I kinda like it, too.
[SHINICHI]
I'm sorry about before.
I didn't mean
to scare you like that.
You're a pretty mysterious guy,
y'know, Shinichi?
Sometimes, I just don't
get you at all.
It's cold out here.
You wanna come over to my place?
So we can talk?
There's nobody else home now.
[SHINICHI]
Your true nature shows
when your life is on the line.
And it turns out,
I'm just pathetic.
All I can think of is that
I don't wanna die.
I want to live!
And I wanna keep living.
I've often told Migi he's
cold‐blooded, but...
but I don't have
any right to say that.
When all's said and done,
I've only made it this far
by stepping on those around me.
[SATOMI] Shinichi...
You're actually a
pretty good guy, aren't you?
The two of us have gone through
a lot together, haven't we?
So even if something
bad happens, we'll be okay.
We can make it.
Murano...
I think that I might...
love you.
[SATOMI] (giggles)
Shinichi, that's a heavy thing
to just drop on a girl.
[SHINICHI] I will live!
I'll do whatever it takes!
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Repose and Awakening"