[TAMURA]
As I recall, your host body
is in its late teens,
is that right?
[SHIMADA]
Yes, that's correct.
Perfect. I can use you then...
Your assignment is to watch the
boy and observe his movements,
but do not kill him.
Is there any point to this?
Yes... While he does pose
something of a threat to us...
he is an exceedingly
valuable resource
in gauging the future
potential of our kind...
Heh!
Shinichi... Izumi...
Got it.
[Kids chatter]
Yo.
Hm? Mitsuo!
Hey, Kana... Ah...
You gonna see your
boyfriend again?
Who?
That piece of shit
who thinks he's
some kinda hero.
Uuh... Just move,
I'm going home.
Wh‐what's with you, Kana?
That hurts, let me go.
Wait, hold on a minute...
Don't tell me you're actually
into that douchebag.
That is really none of
your damn business.
Hmph...
[School bell rings]
Check it out. Look.
Mitsuo?
Hey, loser.
So, didja come by here
to kidnap another girl?
Where's your buddy?
Who?
That poser‐ass "Shinichi"
or whatever.
You looking to start
some trouble punk?
Huh?
Perfect timing.
Hey, Shinichi!
Mitsuo wants to
talk to you.
Huh?
Tsk...
Oh right.
You again, huh?
You n' me.
Need t'talk.
This place again?
Can we please
keep this short?
There's someone
I have to meet.
So, did you and Kana
hook up or what?
Huh? Oh, right.
Kana's that girl
from the other day‐
Don't you play dumb
with me, you asshole!
Listen, you've
got it wrong.
I haven't seen that
girl in a long time,
and I was out of
town before that.
Out of town?!
Anyway, you got
your answer.
Uh... Screw you!
Huh?
[Grunt]
Mmph.
Uh...
Don't... It won't go
like before.
Eat shit!
[Grunting]
Come here!
Uhh...!
[Grunting]
Err‐ya!
Uhh...
Hey! Ohh...
Hey, man... You okay?
[SATOMI]
Shinichi!
Huh?
[Footsteps]
Oh, hey! I was just
at the school
and Kamijo told me
that you... Mm...
It's fine...
Nothing to worry about.
Err...
Here. You can have
your shoe back.
[Sirens in background]
Hey, wanna go in?
I'm pretty hungry.
Uh... Shinichi...
did something happen
to you on your trip?
Huh?
It's just that, you seem
a little different now.
I was just using
my dad's injury
as an excuse to
ditch school
for a while.
Uhh...
Hey, uh...
You are...
Shinichi Izumi...
aren't you?
Well, who's to say?
Ah...
Come on...
Who else would I be?
And you're...
Satomi Murano...
aren't you?
Mm‐hm!
Ah! I can sense him.
He's getting closer!
I'm not sure how I know it,
but he'll come right up
those stairs any second.
There! There he is!
Oh...
[SHINICHI]
I'm home.
[Door closes]
[Door opens]
Dad...
Ah... Shinichi...
You hungry?
I ate...
Did you eat?
No need.
Go easy on the
drinking there...
You should probably get
some food in your stomach.
Yeah...
So I was looking online...
They recommend hiring
a housekeeper for
a time like this.
"Time like this"?
Well, I mean...
Cause Mom... or whoever usually
cooks the meals and stuff
isn't around to do it anymore.
Look boy...
How can you even...
Never mind...
Hire a housekeeper...
I don't really think
I care anymore.
I think I have
some sorta problem.
What's that?
I don't know what's wrong...
I can't cry...
Okay...
Is that all?
I feel like I've
lost something...
Like I'm missing an
important part...
of being human.
Pure foolishness.
[Clicking mouse]
[SHINICHI]
Ever since Migi's cells were
dispersed throughout my body,
my senses have
become heightened.
My hearing. It's stronger.
If I really focus...
[Housewife]
Oh, my! You mean
Mrs. Hashimoto's son?
[Woman]
That's right.
Can you believe it?!
[Car Radio]
And now an update on traffic.
A collision on Metro
Expressway Number Four has...
[Man]
Filthy pigs! Filthy pigs!
Pigs, pigs, pigs, pigs!
[Satomi's heartbeat]
[Loud truck]
Ahh!
Something wrong?
Uh, oh, no,
it's nothing...
Uh!
Wait. What was that?
Shinichi?
I'm sorry, you go on ahead.
Uh... Mm...
It's calling out...
It's asking for help.
Huh?
[SHINICHI]
Can we save it?
[MIGI]
The internal organs
have been crushed,
causing irreparable damage.
Death will occur
within ten minutes.
Ohh...
[SHINICHI]
I'm sorry...
There's nothing we
can do to help you.
Still, this is better
than dying in a dirty,
noisy street, right?
Shinichi?
Unfortunately, this guy's
not gonna make it.
Shinichi... I've been
pretty worried about you.
Why?
'Cause there's
something about you
that's really
different somehow.
You... you used to be more
nervous before, you know?
It was kind of cute
in a weird way,
or maybe comforting,
I guess.
Mm...
But then, ever since you
came back from your trip...
It's like... you've just
been cold and distant.
Maybe I've just been
imagining things...
You seem like yourself now.
It's dead.
Huh?
Its heart stopped.
Let's go...
We're already running late.
[Lid squeaks]
[SATOMI]
Huh! Shinichi?!
Hm?
I don't believe you,
how could you do that?!
You just threw it
in the trash can!
Oh, do you think the
janitor will get mad?
I'm not talking about
the stupid janitor!
The puppy...
It's cruel to that puppy!
I'm not sure how that can
be cruel. The dog's dead.
I know, but Shinichi...
It's already gone...
It's not a dog anymore...
It's just a hunk of
dog‐shaped meat.
Huh?! No!
What's wrong?
I knew you were different!
Before, you never
would've done...
Never...
[Crying]
Murano...
Have I... Have I really
changed that much?
Migi... Migi!
What is it?
Just then... You heard...
I said something
strange to her...
What was it I did wrong?
I don't think you did
anything wrong at all...
From my perspective.
But you are very different now
from how you were before.
Huh?
The statement you just made
about the "dog‐shaped meat"...
Was the sort of thing that I
would be more likely to say.
Oh...
Hm...
I guess so...
Thank you, Migi.
[Digging dirt]
[SHINICHI]
The dog's carcass will break
down and become nutrients
absorbed by this tree.
If I had just done this
in the first place,
Murano wouldn't hate me
so much right now.
Uh...
Oh, Murano.
[Starts to cry]
Ah...
Hm... I guess today's too soon.
I'll give her some
space and try again.
[MIGI]
Shinichi.
Hm?
One of my kind
is here.
Huh?!
[SHINICHI]
Don't tell me
Ryoko Tamiya is back!
[MIGI]
No. This seems to be
someone different.
[SHINICHI]
It can't be Uda and his
Parasite, can it...?
So... does that mean
this one's here to kill me?
[MIGI]
I sense no murderous intent.
What do I do?
For now, I think we should
meet them in a public place.
What? Meet them?!
It's possible this
is not an enemy.
Uh...
Despite being able to
sense our presence,
its rate of approach
is calm and measured.
I believe this may be
another one similar
to Ryoko Tamiya.
In other words, it's the
type that can possibly
be reasoned with.
What's that even
supposed to mean?!
He's here.
Mmh!
So... You're
Shinichi, right?
Yeah who're you?
You're different from how
I'd imagined you would be...
You seem quite strong.
Why're you at my school?
What do you want?
[NAGAI]
Yo, Shinichi.
This guy bothering you?
Haven't seen you around buddy?
D'you just transfer?
Mmph!
Don't interfere.
A‐ahh!
Hideo Shimada...
That is the name you
may use to address me.
Shinichi, I thought
that you...
Rather, that the two of you
and I could be friends.
Who the hell is this?
Ah...
I must go...
Shinichi, would you
please show me the
way to Class Three?
Class Three?
That's Murano's class!
I'm looking forward to
Physical Education...
I believe it's a joint session
between our classes today,
isn't it?
Hm...
[Starting gun shot]
[SHINICHI]
If I go all‐out,
I'd set a world record.
[Grunt]
Mmph!
Ah! Ten point eight seconds?!
No!
Whoa!
[Guys panting]
[YUKO]
It's kinda weird for a transfer
this time of year, isn't it?
I guess so, he said it was
because of his dad's job.
Aww...! This is total bullcrap,
I wish I was in Hide's class.
"Hide"?
Hideo Shimada...
"Hide"!
Seriously, Akiho?
What about Shinichi?
I thought you
liked him?
Yeah. I mean, don't you?
Uh‐What...?!
Come on, gross he's
like a brother to me.
Anyway, it doesn't matter
because he's with Murano now.
Isn't he?
Uh! Well... I...
Hehehe...
[SHIMADA]
Sports are good training.
The more you practice,
the better you become
at controlling your body.
Why drag this out...?
You're planning to attack me
once I let my guard down.
Your assumption is incorrect...
I wonder, if that's what your
right hand believes as well.
Just answer me one question...
Did Ryoko Tamiya send you
to get rid of me?
Ryoko Tamiya?
Ah... she's going by
a different name now.
It's true. She is the one
who told me about you...
but she didn't send me
here to kill you.
In fact, you'll be
pleased to know
that I don't intend to
lay a hand on you,
or anyone in your circle
while I'm here at this school.
And furthermore...
I haven't harmed any humans
for quite some time,
nor do I need to.
Huh?
I've been sustaining myself
on the same sort of
food that humans eat.
If parasites could exist
without killing your kind,
there'd be no problem,
would there?
Like I'd trust you.
The fact is...
we've started to explore
ways in which we can coexist
alongside humans,
within your society.
Given that you two are a
bridge between our two races,
we were hoping that you
would give the idea
some consideration.
Fascinating.
Everything you've
talked about here today
has served to
pique my interest.
[SHIMADA]
It has?
But...
A great deal of it is
difficult to believe.
Oh... really?
Whatever the case,
I do not wish for
conflict either...
So I'd say that's
enough for today...
Let's go, Shinichi.
Huh? Why now?
Mm...
What's the deal...?
We weren't even done
talking to the guy yet.
Shinichi,
I'm going to sleep.
Huh?
You're crashing again?
For four hours...
There's no telling what will
happen if Hideo Shimada
learns of this weakness.
Ah...
Oh...
[SATOMI]
Shinichi...
I can't believe he did that.
But then again, most people
would've just ignored the
puppy in the first place.
Maybe... I shouldn't have
said that he's gotten
cold and distant...
Hm...
[SHINICHI]
What should I do?
If he really is thinking
about coexisting with humans,
then maybe there's a way
we can come up with
something to make it work...
No! I cannot trust those
things. They're merciless!
No matter how
intelligent they are,
they're nothing more than
compassionless insects!
There's no way I'll ever
forget what they've done!
One day, I WILL expose them!
[Angry grunt]
Uh... about the other day...
No, it's fine.
Everything's fine.
Uh‐um...
Well that was great...
I sure have a knack for
screwing things up.
[KANA]
I have... a special power...
it gives me the ability
to sense the presence...
of my soul mate.
[Footsteps]
There he is.
Hello there!
Huh?
Can I help you?
Oh. Wrong person.
I'm so sorry...
I thought you were Shinichi.
Really? What would make you
think that I was Shinichi?
Huh?
When someone mistakes
two people...
it's normally because they look
similar in one way or another.
So... How do Shinichi and
I seem similar to you?
I told you I was sorry.
[KANA]
Hey! What are you doing?!
I know that voice...
Let me go!
I just want to
talk to you
Stop!
for a little bit.
Hey! What're you
doing to her?!
Ah! Let go!
Shinichi!
I only wanted to discuss
some things with her...
It would appear that
this particular female
is rather perceptive.
Listen...
If anything happens to
anyone close to me...
I will be coming after you.
I swear to God
I will take you out.
Hehe. Shinichi.
It's like I keep saying‐
I don't want to fight you.
What's with him...?
There's something cold
in his eyes...
[SHIMADA]
Interesting,
his parasite's signal
seemed very weak
just then.
Oh, wow!
You're pretty strong, huh?
Uhh...
Uh...
[Loudly] Oh, Shinichi!
Walk me to the station!
I'm scared that creepy
guy might be there!
Yeah. No problem.
Ah!
Mm...
Not again!
What the hell?!
What's wrong?
[SHINICHI]
Telepathy?
[KANA]
Yeah. That's right.
I can tell whenever
you're anywhere nearby.
But for some reason, I managed
to get it wrong just then...
But you did
finally show up,
so it's not like
I was totally off.
[SHINICHI]
Yeah, but...
I'm not so sure that's
such a good thing.
Huh?
I mean... whatever it is you
think you're sensing...
it could be some kind of
"wavelengths" being broadcast
by dangerous jerks like him.
So does that mean you're
a dangerous jerk, too?
Uh?!
Uh, well yeah...
yeah I am...
So you should probably
just stay away from guys
like us, you got that?
Hmm...
[SHIMADA]
Well, I think I'll use
this face as bait today.
Hmm... That sow has had
a healthy upbringing,
and its skin has a nice sheen.
Hello there,
are you lost?
Oh!
Well, I was just...
I'd be more than happy
to show you around,
if you'd like me to.
[SHINICHI]
Dad.
Yeah, I know...
Bed time.
'Night.
Shinichi...
Tell me, Son...
When did you suddenly
get to be so strong?
Hm?
It's like you're made of steel.
Like a metal shell with
nothing left on the inside.
Uhh...
I'm sorry.
[Sigh]
[Drawing strokes]
There we go.
Came out even better
than I thought it would.
Heh... Hmm...
[Eating sounds]
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Beyond Good and Evil"