[ABE] They're splitting up.
Which one should I follow?
Yes... Understood.
I'll let you know what I find.
(huh?)
Pickin' up chicks?
(waah!)
Well that's not good.
[ABE] (choking)
I didn't even really notice
that you came up behind me.
[ABE] (struggling &amp; choking)
Ahem... I want you to
help me with something.
[KURAMORI] The last I heard,
he was headed for this
building's basement.
But I'm not crazy enough to
go in there by myself,
so I was kinda hoping
you guys would‐
[MIGI] What did we say?
We explicitly told you
not to go after this one.
[SHINICHI] Well?
Do you sense anything?
[MIGI] No, none of my kind
are currently in the area.
I don't get it.
Where is he?
Something smells
really bad in here.
Huh?
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
Oh, my God... Not again!
Shinichi, one of them is coming.
[KURAMORI] (gasps)
Two hundred meters...
One hundred eighty meters...
Very fast.
It's probably in a car.
If we leave now, we'll likely
run into it near the entrance.
God, this is bad!
C'mon, we gotta hide!
It has another human.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
[WOMAN] Eew, gross.
What is this place?
[KAWADA] Oh, never mind that.
Please just stand right over
there, if you don't mind.
[WOMAN] Oh, like this?
[KAWADA] Yes, that's fine.
What's this about?
You're so weird.
[MIGI]
Don't make a move, Shinichi.
[KAWADA] Why are you hiding?
Well, whatever.
Now then...
Let me get a look at you.
[KURAMORI] This is it.
This is how they eat people.
Stop right there!
[KUROMORI] (gasps)
[WOMAN] (gasps) Who is that?!
Who are you?
I can tell you're not one of us.
Careful, lady!
That guy's not really a human!
Get away from him!
[WOMAN] Huh?
[SHINICHI] Hurry! He brought
you here to kill you!
(screams)
You son of a bitch!
You're a filthy human.
Listen to me, Shinichi.
You have to forget
that I'm even here.
[MIGI]
He'll defeat us before we can
finish discussing how
to coordinate.
[MIGI] You can see his
blades' movements, right?
[SHINICHI] Yeah!
[KURAMORI] I don't...
Everything's moving so fast!
[MIGI]
Just keep dodging his strikes.
And don't even think
of trying to attack this one
like you did last time.
Can we really
beat him like this?!
Well done,
your moves are quite good.
I'll win this by having
the better steed.
Did you just call me a steed?!
(aahhh...)
(ungh)
(gurgle)
(gapsing for breath)
(panting)
(aahhh...)
(urk!)
(heavy breathing)
(ugghhh...)
[MIGI] Our weakness is below
the neck; the human portion.
If we can protect that,
we will ultimately win.
[SHINICHI] I couldn't save her.
And it's too late now.
I knew what was going on.
But instead I...
I spent... I spent too much
time doing nothing!
[MIGI] In any case,
this whole thing is bad news.
Judging from the man's actions,
this structure must be one of
the communal dining areas
established by Hirokawa.
And if that's true,
it could mean that
we've just committed
a clear act of aggression
against the mayor's faction.
Are you listening, Shinichi?
[KURAMORI] (vomiting)
[SHINICHI] I was wrong.
[MIGI] Hmm?
I was so wrong.
[MIGI]
Shinichi, we need to leave this
place as soon as possible.
So, what now?
I mean, you're not going
to stop looking, are you?
(huh?)
There's a detective
I met a while back,
I believe his name was Hirama.
I'm sure he'll listen to
whatever you have to say.
Because, not long ago,
he suspected me
of being one of them.
Hey now, don't give him
any strange ideas.
What's strange about it?
We're trying to go up
against Hirokawa.
What're you saying?
Have you not realized
that we could be
in an extremely precarious
situation right now?
[SHINICHI]
We can use the video he recorded
to get the police to search
the building from top to bottom.
Don't be foolish.
We are in that video footage,
too, you know.
Look, I don't even care
about that anymore!
Do you want your father
to be murdered as well?
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
What's that s'posta mean?!
Why would you say that?!
[KURAMORI]
You don't have to worry.
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
[KURAMORI] I was wrong, okay?
I'm in way over my head here,
just like my wife told me.
A small‐timer like me shouldn't
have gotten involved with this
to begin with.
(crack!)
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
I' m gonna get rid of
every bit of evidence
I've managed to find so far.
How could you?
You saw what happened!
Are you trying to say none of it
means anything to you?
Of course, it does!
Dammit, yes! Look at me,
I'm still shaking here!
But anybody who saw that
and honestly thinks he
could fight it
is out of his freaking mind!
Maybe you don't get it.
You're not a normal
human being anymore!
Look the fight that I just
witnessed back there,
that was two monsters
trying to kill each other.
I'm only a simple,
normal person.
I'm not that brave, and I don't
have any special power crap
to protect myself.
I can't do all that, okay?
As of today, I'm gonna forget
about the monsters and
Reiko Tamura...
and you too.
(sighs)
C'mon, don't look at me
like that.
I have a wife and kid to
think about, all right?
I know I got a little
high and mighty,
talking about the good of
humanity and stuff, but this...
this is too much.
Well, I guess that's true
human nature for you.
Shut the hell up.
(dog barking)
[KURAMORI]
Maybe you don't get it!
You're not a normal
human being anymore!
[SHINICHI]
He's absolutely right.
I'm NOT normal anymore.
The things I can sense...
The things I can do...
Shinichi...
I've said this many times now,
but we should avoid
futile resistance.
Futile?
Yeah, maybe.
But well, we did win today,
right?
We can beat them one‐on‐one!
That is the answer!
If I were to choose to
cooperate with you, that is.
(huh?)
(piano playing softly)
[SHINICHI] I can do it...
I can do it!
If I put my mind to it,
I can do anything!
(piano continues playing)
One at a time...
Yes,
I can get them one at a time!
I'll beat them alone
if I have to.
I don't need to ask
any more humans for help.
That way,
I'm sure Migi would help me.
No...
I will make him help me!
(piano continues playing)
Call it my human ego
or whatever,
but I wanna save
as many people as I can!
And it'll make things safer
for Murano, too.
(piano continues playing)
[YUKO] Did you and Shinichi
have a fight or something?
I haven't seen you together
lately.
[SATOMI]
Not so much a fight as...
Well, I don't know.
It's like we just can't really
trust each other or something.
(huh?)
I don't know,
it looks like HE trusts YOU.
(piano continues playing)
(self‐conscious chuckle)
(ah!)
[SATOMI] I... I gotta go!
[YUKO] Murano, wait!
Seriously?
[YUKO] Shut up, Akiho.
I will protect
every person I can!
(piano continues playing)
Our enemy is strong.
We cannot allow him
to roam free.
[TAMURA]
Killing him would be a waste.
Though I care nothing
for the detective.
Unwise...
He is, without a doubt
very dangerous to us.
Why would you defend him?
We are not human beings, are we?
Why would our opinions be in
such opposition to one another?
Now then...
I understand you're currently
raising a human child.
Could that be affecting
your judgment?
Why not simply dispose of it?
I can't do that just yet.
At any rate,
Shinichi Izumi killed one of
our members in a dining area.
We can't just let this go,
obviously.
We will need to eliminate him.
Very well, then.
But I would like to make sure
that his body
is returned to me fully intact.
[HIROKAWA] For what purpose?
[TAMURA] I want to dissect him.
(lone person clapping)
[HIROKAWA]
Very impressive, Mr. Goto.
Was it Mozart?
[GOTO] No, Chopin.
Our target is purported
to be formidable.
Granted, I think it should be
you who takes care of him.
If you're implying Miki
wants to do it,
I will allow him to try.
He could use some more study.
[SHINICHI] (echoing)
What is this?
Who are you?
[MONSTER MIGI] Things are rough
for me, too, you know?
[SHINICHI] (echoing)
You... You're a monster!
(bones clicking)
Hmm?
Ah,
so I look like a monster to you?
But you're in
no position to talk.
[MIGI] Just take a look at this,
Shinichi.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
(screams)
What... What the hell was that?
[clock ticking loudly]
I need to kill off the
parasites by attacking
them one at a time.
But how am I ever going
to get Migi to agree to it?
Maybe the best way would be
to make it so that we have
no choice...
that we have to fight.
(school bell chiming)
What're you doing?
I'm gonna be late for class.
[MIGI] You don't have time.
I sense my kind.
What? Again?!
Here's my chance!
Okay, let's fight.
Where is it right now?
[MIGI] Don't be so eager.
WE are being targeted this time.
The signal's headed straight
for us right now with
intent to kill.
I sense three.
There's three of 'em.
O'kay.
Do we fight, or do we run?
You seem more than ready
for a fight, at the moment.
If so, this is
the ideal location.
[SHINICHI] Don't be ridiculous!
I will NOT do this at school!
Shinichi!
It's okay.
You don't have to worry, Murano.
Huh?
It'sokay!
Look, you don't have to worry.
(gasps) Don't tell me...
[SHINICHI] (ungh!)
Shinichi?
(running footsteps)
[MIGI] Stop; I've lost them.
They're more than
300 meters away now,
and they seem to be on foot.
So there's three coming
for us at once?
[MIGI] In this case,
we should consider taking
them out one‐by‐one,
rather than opposing
all of them together.
Take them out one by one...
Okay, I'm ready to go!
[MIGI] No, never mind.
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
Forget about that strategy.
Migi, why?!
[MIGI] I'm tired.
It's time for me to sleep.
(huh?!)
You've got to be shitting me?!
It can't be helped.
It's a case of
simple physiology.
In any case,
you have to keep moving,
as straightforward as possible.
That's all we can do for now.
So then, I'm on my own
for four hours?
(train horn)
(sighs) Well, I guess I can
relax a bit for now.
Two more hours, huh?
I should be able
to shake them off.
A taxi? Seriously?
You can keep the change.
Thanks a lot.
Only one, huh?
So, it's not him.
[MIKI] Well, hello there!
Nice place, huh?
No one around,
and it's so quiet.
He's smiling.
There's no way this
guy's a parasite.
I'm kinda surprised.
You took off in quite a panic
back there, didn't you?
And I had heard
you were so tough.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
So what's goin' on? Huh?
You know, your hand's signal
seems awfully weak at the‐
(huh?)
[MIKI] Hey! Wait up!
(chuckles)
I've never seen a parasite as
expressive as that before!
But he is pretty slow.
Parasites should be able
to get more
from their host‐body potential.
Still, the other two
could be close by.
I can't let my guard down!
(panting)
Where ya headed to, young fella?
Would you like a lift somewhere?
Yeah, thank you so much.
Is he... is this guy...
or his dog...
are they parasites?!
No, it's too small.
[OLD GUY] Are you sure
you wanna get out here?
Yeah, I can't thank you enough,
sir.
Thank God!
I guess he was okay.
It's been almost
four hours now.
It looks like they've given up.
(vehicle approaching)
(ah!)
Please, Migi, wake up.
[MIKI] (ungh!)
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
Whoa, whoa, whoa! (umphf)
(laughs)
[SHINICHI] Migi? Migi!
WAKE UP!
(sleepily) (unh?) Ah, Shinichi,
I'm so glad to see
you're all right.
Huh?
They're here!
That's right.
But I still haven't
been able to find
where the other two
are hiding yet.
[MIGI]
I don't think you understand.
All three of them
are in that one body.
Huh?!
Did you seriously name
your parasite "Migi"?
What a coincidence!
Well... (chuckles)
You are simply NOT
gonna believe this.
Ya'see, I'm called "Miki."
With a 'K'.
(ungh!)
Well, this is interesting.
(chuckling)
Ya'can't beat me.
(chuckles)
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Happy Family"