[ICHIGO] After the successful
kissing with Plantation 26,
Squad 13 was rewarded
with a special vacation.
[ALL gasp]
[ZOROME, FUTOSHI]
It's the ocean!
[ZOROME, FUTOSHI shouting]
So childish. Just 'cause
we're on break
doesn't mean we
should act stupid.
I don't blame them. After all,
this is our first time seeing
an ocean that's
okay to swim in.
That's true.
I didn't know a place like this
survived on the surface.
[ICHIGO] Ever since being
assigned to the squad,
we'd been living under
extreme anxiety and stress.
But this scene was entirely
removed from all that,
which put everybody
in high spirits.
Hey! Don't go too far
out there, guys, okay?
Nana said that she'd come pick
us up tomorrow morning.
[GORO] Do you think this
is some kind of training?
[ICHIGO]
Who knows?
[ICHIGO] But... his place seems
to be free of klaxosaurs,
so as long as we're here,
we might as well
enjoy ourselves, right?
Uh, yeah.
Darling, let's go!
[HIRO gasps]
Look at him. I'm glad that
Hiro's all better now.
Turns out we were
worried for nothing.
But, now we know that
rumor was false,
and Hiro's finally become
an actual parasite.
Good news all around, I'd say.
[ICHIGO]
Following that last battle,
the two of them were
made official partners.
I still have my misgivings about
Zero Two, but one look at Hiro
now makes it obvious that she
was exactly what he needed.
[ICHIGO chuckles]
I'm really glad.
♪
[MALE SAGE A] Who could've
imagined that failure
of a special specimen would have
so much ability within him?
[MALE SAGE C]
Seriously.
I wish he had shown us
this from the start.
[MALE SAGE B] At least our
girl's silly search for a man
has finally come to an end.
We should be happy about that.
[FEMALE SAGE A] True, but it
doesn't change the fact that
she still needs to
be monitored closely.
[PAPA]
Plantation 13 is hereby declared
a top-priority
surveillance project.
Code Zero-One-Six will be
tasked with bringing our girl
to the Grand Crevasse
safe and sound.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
The time has finally come.
[NANA]
A special surveillance subject?
Is this because Zero Two
is now officially under
Plantation 13's purview?
[HACHI] One of APE's
special forces has become
an exclusive parasite
of a plantation.
There's no precedent here,
but it was the obvious decision.
[FRANXX] Ah, Zero Two.
Glad to see you're okay.
[ZERO TWO] I am okay, and it's
all thanks to my darling.
You didn't have to
bother coming here.
We would've been fine.
[FRANXX]
Don't be like that.
[NANA]
Hiro, this is Dr. Franxx.
Creator of the FRANXX.
The creator.
Yes, and this here is--
[9'a]
No need to introduce us.
I'm sure that someday soon,
we're bound to run
into one another again.
This is the first time
anyone's survived Zero Two.
Huh. So this is
what you're like.
Must say, I've taken an
interest in you guys.
Doctor. As of today, Strelizia
and Code Zero-Zero-Two
have been transferred into
Plantation 13's purview.
[FRANXX] Yes, yes, I know.
The geezers told me already.
With that,
I hereby announce that Code
Zero-One-Six has officially
been appointed Zero-Zero-Two's
partner going forward.
Oh, yes, sir!
Oh, Darling! I'm so happy!
--[ZERO TWO giggles]
--[HIRO] Easy. I can't breathe.
[ZERO TWO]
Hey, Doctor.
I'll be fine. As long as I'm
with my darling, we've got this.
[HACHI]
One often needs foreign elements
to adapt to their environment.
Guess that's what this
special order's for.
Yes, but...
...sending the children
to the beach by themselves?
The doctor's ideas are
always so unconventional.
[KOKORO]
Here I go!
Bring it!
'Kay, ready? And... there!
[FUTOSHI sighs] The beach
is pretty great, isn't it?
Yeah it is.
[MIKU giggles]
[ZOROME]
Curious.
Dunno why, but the girls look
50 percent cuter here.
[GORO] Yeah, this is certainly
a sight for sore eyes.
Hold on a second, Goro.
The way you're talking,
it almost sounds like
you're one of us.
[ZOROME] I thought you
double-digits were just
a bunch of goody-two-shoes,
but we may actually have
something in common.
What the hell? I'm still
a guy just like you are!
How am I supposed to ignore
this marvelous view?
[GIRLS yelp]
[BOYS]
Huh?
[KOKORO] Ow. Are you
all right, Miku?
Sorry, I was looking
up the whole time.
Uh? That string's coming undone.
[MIKU] Oh, no! Can you
tie it back up for me?
ALL]
All hail the glorious beach!
Wait up. How far out
are you planning to go?
Yo, guys, check out those two.
[ZERO TWO sighs] Swimming in
the ocean feels so good.
And it does taste salty.
It's the real deal
this time, huh, darling?
Is something wrong?
Oh, sorry. It's just, looking
at you in a swimsuit's...
What, weird?
[HIRO]
No, you look really good!
But for some reason, I can't
look you in the eye right now.
[ZERO TWO]
But you saw me naked before.
It's not like I
meant to, though!
[ZERO TWO] Darling, you're the
one who helped me get here.
'Til now, I'd never taken
a dip in a real ocean.
You truly are my
wings, aren't you?
If I'm with you, I can
fly anywhere I want.
Say, darling?
The two of us, we'll always
be together, won't we?
[HIRO]
"Always."
[FRANXX]
Code Zero-One-Six.
Let me offer you
a piece of advice.
[HIRO]
Yes, sir?
[FRANXX] Don't let her
consume your emotions, too.
That is, if you want to
always be her partner.
Otherwise, you'll be
the one to suffer later.
You know, darling, you and I
have crossed a line together.
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO giggles]
Just like before,
your taste really does
makes my heart race.
Were you expecting a kiss?
A kiss is a declaration that
the other person belongs to you.
So you should only ever kiss
the person you love. Got it?
Only who you "love"?
Wait, hold on a second.
Have you done it with someone
other than me, perhaps?
Uh, well, I, uh...
[HIRO gasps, yelps]
Darling?
[HIRO grunts]
[BOYS chattering]
[IKUNO]
Ichigo?
Distracted?
[ICHIGO gasps]
[IKUNO giggles]
By the ocean, I mean.
Aren't you going in the water?
You were always good
at swimming. So good.
[ICHIGO]
Oh, that's what you meant.
Well... I dunno,
I haven't decided.
[IKUNO] I brought a book,
so don't worry about me.
Go on, have fun.
Thank you, Ikuno, I will.
[MITSURU] You came all
this way just to read?
Should I force myself
to frolic? I'll pass.
Hey, no arguments from me.
[BOYS chattering]
[MITSURU]
Isn't it great?
Not too long ago, the kid
looked like he wanted to die,
and now he's a part
of the group again.
Funny how fast things change.
Please don't come looking
to me for affirmation.
I'm not like you, Mitsuru.
Oh, sorry. I was just
thinking out loud.
If that's all you wanted
to say, then are we done here?
[MITSURU] Nah. I found something
that's pretty interesting.
[HIRO grunts]
What's gotten into you guys?
[GORO] I didn't wanna intrude
on you but, you know,
these two wouldn't listen to me.
Uh. What is it you want?
What the heck is a kiss?
Huh? You were listening to us?
A "kiss."
We've never heard that
word used that way before,
but it sounds so magical!
[ZOROME] Where're you goin',
Hiro my boy?
It's startin' to look like
you're hiding something.
[FUTOSHI] What were you
guys getting up to?
Huh? We weren't doing
anything. Goro. Help.
[GORO] Hiro, I also wanna
know what a kiss is.
[HIRO]
Not you, too!
I don't fully
understand it myself...
But it seems to be when
two people stick...
..their mouths together.
[ZOROME, GORO, FUTOSHI]
Their mouths?!
Hold on a second!
You mean mouths can be used
for something besides eating?
Did you forget about
breathing and talking?
And what exactly happens when
you do kiss or whatever?
Well. I guess it felt
really warm and soft.
And it, uh...
made my heart race.
But, we didn't kiss
back there, all right?!
Wow, I wanna try it for myself.
[ZOROME shouts] I need to
know what it feels like!
Damn it, Hiro! You got
the jump on us yet again!
[ZOROME grunts]
You hafta let me kiss you!
[HIRO]
Huh?!
Wait! You should only do it
with the person you love!
[ZOROME]
The heck is a "person you love"?
What are you guys doing?
Don't try to stop me.
[BOTH yelp]
[ZOROME]
Ow!
Hey, do you know
what a kiss is, Ichigo?
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
[FUTOSHI] The thing where two
people touch mouths together.
[ICHIGO gasps]
Nope!
[MIKU]
Hey!
There's something
you've gotta see!
[ZOROME]
Huh...?
Hey, are you sure about this?
[MITSURU]
Yeah.
You'll be able to see it when
we get to the end of this path.
It's like some kind
of exploration! Ha! Too cool!
Maybe. But it's so dark in here,
I'm getting a
little creeped out.
You do know you didn't
have to come along
if you didn't want to.
[KOKORO]
Hm?
Don't talk to Kokoro like that!
She doesn't deserve it!
You don't get it.
I can't guarantee anyone's
safety from here on out.
[GORO] Is there a relationship
closer than being partners?
[HIRO]
Huh?
[GORO] Oh. Sorry, watching you
two makes me wonder.
You talk about things like,
"kisses" and
"the person you love."
What's that all about?
I don't get it at all.
Honestly, I don't really
understand, either.
"Made your heart race," huh?
You know, I have a lot
of fun being with Ichigo,
but sometimes it
hurts a bit, too.
I dunno, maybe I'm
not like you guys.
[IKUNO]
Ichigo?
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
[IKUNO] What's the matter?
Your face is all red.
Oh, is it really?
[MITSURU]
We can see it now.
What is this place?
[IKUNO] It's like a small
city or something.
[ZOROME]
A city? This?
It's nothing like the cities
that the adults live in!
[KOKORO] Do you think there
are people living here?
[MITSURU]
Who knows?
Though I've certainly never
heard of anybody living outside
of the plantations before.
[ZOROME]
Hey! Is there anybody here?
Gotta tell ya, this really
isn't what I was expecting.
Oh, yeah? And what exactly
were you expecting?
[ZOROME]
Look at it!
This place isn't all
that different from our
boarding house, don't ya think?
You're right.
It's like this was
the model they used
to build the environment
we live in.
[MIKU]
Okay, but why?
[IKUNO]
Beats me.
[FUTOSHI]
Hm. Hey, where's Kokoro?
[creaking footsteps]
[KOKORO]
Huh?
A baby?
[MITSURU]
Kokoro!
[KOKORO]
Huh? Ah!
Please don't wander off
on your own like that.
It's like I told you earlier.
I can't guarantee your safety.
Oh... I'm sorry.
A kiss. Putting lips together.
That's right. I've done
it with my darling.
[ICHIGO gasps]
Zero Two.
What is it you've
done with Hiro?
[ZERO TWO]
Kissed.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[ZERO TWO giggles] I guess you
guys aren't ready for it yet.
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ICHIGO] Shows what you know.
I've done it, too.
Yeah? With whom?
A real kiss, is shared
with your special someone.
So, tell me. Is the person
you kissed special to you?
Uh, well, that's...
[GORO]
Ichigo?
[HIRO gasps]
[MIKU sighs]
Oh, man, I am totally beat!
[KOKORO]
We did do a lot of walking.
[MIKU] I'm gonna be
so sore tomorrow.
[KOKORO giggles]
I wonder. What was
this place, anyway?
Well, if nothing else,
we can be sure it was part of
civilization at some point.
[GORO] So, people lived
here in the past?
[ZERO TWO]
They abandoned it.
[HIRO]
Huh?
Humans used to live
on the surface,
until they abandoned it.
There are tons of places like
this, all around the world.
[ZOROME]
Woohoo! The food's ready!
[ZOROME, FUTOHI chatter]
Interesting. When did all
of this stuff get here?
[FUTOSHI]
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Come on, you gotta
be more careful.
[ICHIGO]
You okay?
[FUTOSHI chuckles]
Yeah, I'm fine.
[GORO]
Here. You should have some.
[ZOROME sighs]
[ZOROME]
Whoa. It's starting to bubble!
Cool! Let me give it a try!
[ZERO TWO]
Hey, darling.
I'm gonna go swim
some more, okay?
You wanna swim when
it's this dark?
Uh-huh.
[MIKU] I'm stuffed!
My belly's gonna explode!
[KOKORO] Goodness, Miku.
Everyone's looking.
Where are your manners?
[MIKU] After how much walking I
did today, I couldn't care less.
They can stare all they want.
Fact is, I've got the lap
and they're jealous!
[FUTOSHI, ZOROME growl]
[ZOROME] Hey, we walked
just as much as you did!
[FUTOSHI]
This isn't fair!
[MIKU]
Yeah, yeah, keep whining.
[ZOROME]
Aw!
[HIRO]
Why do you think humanity
abandoned the surface?
You talkin' about what
Zero Two said earlier?
Who could really say?
There must be some reason they
couldn't live here anymore.
[HIRO] But there's so much more
space and beautiful scenery.
I'm shocked to learn there's
a world like this outside.
[FUTOSHI] We have all that stuff
in Mistilteinn, too, though.
And besides, the outside world
is filled with klaxosaurs.
But what if humanity had never
started extracting magma energy.
Do you think the klaxosaurs
would still have shown up?
[MITSURU] You're doubting
Papa and the rest?
The threat of the klaxosaurs
is why they moved into
the plantations in
the first place.
Is that not a noble cause?
[ZOROME shouts]
Papa and the others are amazing!
I mean, to think,
the adults used to live
in these drab outdoors,
but now, they get to live
in bright, sparkling cities!
[FUTOSHI]
Yeah, you're right.
[ZOROME] And we're the ones
protecting their lifestyles!
We're useful to them. Is there
anything better than that?
As long as we keep
killing the klaxosaurs,
we'll have plenty of
food on our table,
and Papa will pay
attention to us!
And then, one day, we'll surely
become adults, too!
Heck yeah!
[ZOROME] Well? You agree
with me, don't'cha?
Oh. Uh...
C'mon, man. Why're you so down?
You can talk to your teammates.
Teammates?
What? Did I say something
weird and not realize it?
Zorome aside, I've gotta say.
Seeing as you guys
are the newbies,
you'd better earn your keep,
but you specifically have to
make up for Naomi's absence.
As for myself, I find
it very reassuring
that the both of
you are with us.
Same goes for me. Zero Two's
already helped us out a bunch.
Well, you heard 'em.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro.
Please allow me to officially
welcome you and Zero Two
as members of Squad 13.
It's good to have you.
But fair warning, as leader, I'm
going to work you to the bone.
So be prepared.
[ZOROME chuckles]
Thanks, guys.
It means a lot,
and I'll do my best.
You better! Welcome aboard!
Glad to finally
make it official!
[ZERO TWO sighs]
[ZOROME]
Hey, guys, look! It's a crab!
[FUTOSHI]
What? Where? Is it edible?
[MITSURU] How are you still
hungry after all that food?
There's one over there, too!
Hold it right there, crab!
[rustling]
[ICHIGO gasps]
Sorry. I hope
I didn't wake you up.
[ICHIGO] I couldn't
sleep for some reason.
[HIRO]
Yeah, same.
I felt like it'd be a
waste to fall asleep.
Ooh, look up, Hiro!
You can see so many stars!
[HIRO]
Wow, you're right.
Hey, there's Orion.
[HIRO] In the past, Orion was
considered the most prominent
winter constellation.
Really? Back when
we were little,
you'd tell me about
the stars all the time.
[HIRO]
Did I?
Yeah, you did!
I might be stupid, but I still
remember everything you
taught me growing up, Hiro.
Hmph.
So, did you forget
about that star, too?
[HIRO]
You mean the Ichigo star?
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
The 15th of Orion,
same as your code number.
I read in a book once that it's
so dim, it can be difficult to
spot with the naked eye, which
is why we can't see it now.
But we promised we'd see
it together one day,
after leaving the Garden.
What the heck? So you
do remember just fine.
[HIRO grunts]
[ICHIGO] We can look for
the star again sometime.
I mean, we are gonna be fighting
on the same team from now on.
[HIRO]
That's true.
I know that earlier I acted
all bossy and told you
to be prepared. But the rest
of us are gonna have to step up
and do our best, too.
You know. I'm going to
try my hardest as leader,
so don't give all your
attention to Zero Two.
Look at me from
time to time, as well.
[ICHIGO] Also... About our
kiss during the mock battle.
I see it as something special!
And, I... wanna be with you--
Ichigo, look! Shooting stars!
[ICHIGO gasps]
[HIRO chuckles]
[ICHIGO] With their long tails,
the shooting stars
blazed a trail across the sky.
Drawn in by gravity, those stars
were shining so brightly,
just like us. And the
light they gave off
looked to me like
gentle rays of hope.
[HIRO] They say if you make
a wish on a shooting star,
it'll come true.
So, what would you wish for?
[ICHIGO grunts] I was
trying to tell you before.
[HIRO]
Uh?
[ICHIGO giggles]
Stupid Hiro.
[HIRO]
H-Hey, what the heck?
[ICHIGO]
That night,
I wished on the shooting stars
for that light to never...
...ever fade.
♪