[HIRO] The nestlings had a
dream of soaring the skies.
[ICHIGO]
A name?
Yeah, I gave myself a name,
and you should have one, too!
Mine's Hiro.
[ICHIGO]
But why am I "Ichigo"?
[HIRO] Because that's what came
to mind when I thought about
your code number.
[ICHIGO gasps]
So, that's my name now?
[BOY A]
Hey, what about me?
[GIRL A]
Yeah, I want one.
[HIRO]
Within their dark, cramped nest,
they clung to one another.
Waiting for parents who
would never return.
[MITSURU] Um... can you
give me a name, too?
Sure thing!
[HIRO chuckles]
[HIRO]
But we believed...
...that great blue skies
awaited us outside.
♪
[HIRO gasps]
All done?
[HIRO] Yeah. They said they
didn't find anything wrong.
Oh. That's good.
[HIRO]
Um.
--Ichi--
--[NANA] Ichigo. Get ready.
[ICHIGO]
Roger.
[NANA] He's the first sample
who's ever piloted with her
and taken so little damage.
[HACHI] He failed to common
connect with Delphinium,
and yet, somehow, he was
compatible with Strelizia,
despite being unconscious.
The only thing that
could explain it is...
The special specimen.
[GORO] Hey, did something happen
between you two in the cockpit?
[HIRO]
Why do you ask?
[GORO] Well, it's just, Ichigo
was acting a little weird
after the mock battle.
Now that you mention it,
she did seem mad earlier.
Yeah, well, you know how she is.
That girl's always gotten too
worked up when it comes to you.
[HIRO]
She has?
There aren't many like you
with codes in the teens.
You're basically siblings.
And you've always been together.
With me, too, of course.
It's a miracle that all three
of us from the special class
got assigned to here.
I mean, what're the odds?
Siblings, huh?
That's true.
I guess you're right.
Hey, Goro?
[GORO]
Hm?
[HIRO] Seeing as you're
Ichigo's partner,
could you tell her that it
wasn't her fault for me?
Sure, I don't have a
problem doing that.
But what'll you do
after this last attempt?
Well, I'll try to ride
with Zero Two again.
[GORO] Hiro. You've heard
the rumors about her, right?
[HIRO] What, that nobody's
ever piloted with her
more than three times?
A rumor's all it is.
Didn't you say you
saw what happened
to her previous partner?
Please, just--
[HIRO]
Look, Goro.
It's not complicated.
If Zero Two's the only
one I can ride with,
then I just have
to ride with her.
Our purpose in life is
to pilot the FRANXX.
It's why we were born.
[FUTOSHI] What happened to
all that talk about Hiro still
having a shot at
becoming a parasite.
[IKUNO] Considering he was only
able to connect for a moment,
I don't like his chances.
No way he's getting in
with that weak shit.
[MITSURU] Then what's that
say about the parasites
who could only manage
a draw against him?
Whoa. I can't be held
accountable for that.
Miku's the one who
made us fall over.
[MIKU gasps]
Excuse me,
do you not remember what
you said right before that?
Nah, I try to live in
the "now," unlike you.
Unbelievable.
You two shouldn't fight.
It hurts your numbers.
Anyway. If a parasite
can't pilot,
there's little hope Papa
will be willing to accept it.
[KOKORO sighs]
[FUTOSHI]
She's right.
We saw so many kids disappear
from the Garden because of that.
And it was so sad.
Ichigo isn't much
better, though.
She's s'posed to be our leader,
but her friendship with
Hiro gets in the way.
Honestly, I have no idea
how Goro puts up with it.
[ICHIGO]
What's Goro have to do with it?
[GORO]
Hm? Uh, what about me?
If Hiro becomes a parasite,
it'll help us out.
That's all there is to it.
[MIKU]
I hate to break it to you,
but that's a pretty big "if."
[ICHIGO]
He still has a chance.
[MIKU]
I'm not so sure.
He couldn't even get
the job done with you.
At this point, I think
it's over for the guy.
[ICHIGO] Don't forget,
he did pilot Strelizia.
Even if he was unconscious at
the time, he saved us all.
[ICHIGO]
I still believe in him.
[MITSURU]
Ichigo.
While I can understand why you
would want to stick up for him,
he did nothing.
Hiro was just a passenger
taken along for the ride.
We don't know that!
We have no idea what happened!
There's no doubt
Hiro was special.
Even among the double-digits,
he was a cut above.
We all thought he
would lead us.
That he'd be the one
to show us the way.
But life had other plans.
Hiro wasn't able to
become a parasite.
Let's face it, he's not
who he used to be.
[ICHIGO grunts]
[MITSURU] It's time to
give up and cut our losses.
I don't wanna see this
pathetic side of Hiro anymore.
[ZERO TWO]
Darling, you pervert.
[HIRO]
Huh?
Quit staring at me, already.
[HIRO]
Oh, sorry!
[ZERO TWO giggles]
It's fine.
The doctor says parasites are
actually better off being
a little pervy.
[HIRO] But how does
staring make me a pervert?
[grunts]
About time you got
done. Let's go.
[HIRO]
Huh? Go where?
[alarm beeps]
Uh, we children
have restrictions
on where we're allowed to go.
Most of this area's
off-limits to us.
[ZERO TWO]
Oh?
[HIRO gasps]
You have an S-class ID?
Uh, hey, what're--?
[ZERO TWO] If we just go
through together, like this...
I got in?
See? No problem.
[HIRO]
Wow!
[HIRO] How do you
know about this place?
[ZERO TWO]
All the plantations have
pretty much the same design.
This is nothing special.
If you say so.
Thing is, I've never set
foot in the city before.
All we've ever known
is the birdcage
and a few other facilities.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[ZERO TWO] Why are you
staring at me again?
Because I'm trying to
think of a name for you.
[ZERO TWO]
A name?
[HIRO] Yeah, I'm really
good at naming people.
[ZERO TWO scoffs]
Well, I'm fine with Zero Two.
[HIRO]
But doesn't it feel kinda lame
just going by your code number?
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[HIRO gasps]
Hey. Careful!
[ZERO TWO] Once we die,
all we'll be is a statistic.
It won't matter
what we were called.
Look at it. This lifeless city.
There're no skies
or oceans here.
It's isolated at the end of
a one-way street to nowhere.
Standing there's
not safe! Come back!
[ZERO TWO]
Say, darling?
Do you wanna run away with me?
I can get you out of
here if you would like.
[HIRO grunts, gasps]
Just... kidding.
[HACHI] We've received
orders to sortie from HQ.
[FUTOSHI gasps]
They want us to fight already?
There's no need to be nervous.
You won't be battling klaxosaurs
like the one the
other day just yet.
Oh, thank goodness.
[NANA] We would've liked to
ease you in more gradually,
but unfortunately,
we can't afford to.
[HACHI] You'll be facing
a Conrad-class klaxosaur.
It's just a little bit
smaller than a FRANXX.
Klaxosaurs are attracted
to magma-energy reactions.
Lately, they've been showing
up deep in a Level Eight mine
on the outskirts, wreaking all
kinds of havoc there.
Even the automatic bulwark
systems can't keep up with them.
[NANA]
We should mention that Strelizia
won't be a part of this mission.
[gasps]
After all, you parasites are
going to have to defend
Plantation 13 by
yourselves eventually.
[NANA] If you can't
eliminate this klaxosaur,
there's no way you can
handle any in the future.
So just focus on
the task at hand.
Ichigo and Goro will have
command in the field.
[BOTH]
Right.
[HACHI] That's it.
All hands, prepare to board.
[GORO] Are you still upset
about the mock battle?
'Cause we're going
into actual combat now.
Gotta switch gears.
[ICHIGO]
Yeah. I know.
Hey.
[GORO]
Huh?
[ICHIGO]
I'll do my best as leader.
You take care of the handling.
[GORO]
Sure thing. Let's do this.
[ZOROME]
Finally, my first battle!
Just try not to get
so full of yourself
you blow it like last time.
Relax! I've got this!
[laughs]
Well, I'm not so sure
you've got anything.
[GORO]
Ready, Ichigo?
[ICHIGO]
Yeah. Come to me.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[IKUNO grunts]
[HACHI]
What's wrong, Chlorophytum?
Seems Ikuno's not up to it.
I'm almost there,
just give me a second!
Don't bother. It's over.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] It appears,
their para-capacity's too low,
and still falling.
No go, huh?
[HACHI]
Chlorophytum will stay behind.
The other three will
go on without it.
[ICHIGO]
Roger that.
[NANA]
This might be tough.
[KOKORO]
That's a big hole.
How far down do
you think it goes?
[ZOROME] Do you see
that pipe? It's a monster!
[GORO] They used these to
extract the magma reserves?
[HACHI]
Head down to Level Eight.
As you're well aware by now,
in order to completely
neutralize a klaxosaur,
you must first
extract its core,
which is essentially its heart,
and then shatter it using your
customized magma-energy weapons.
If the core's destroyed,
so is the klaxosaur.
Got that?
[ALL]
Roger!
[ICHIGO]
Proceeding to objective.
Both of you, fall in
behind Delphinium.
[KOKORO]
Got it.
[ICHIGO]
Miku?
[MIKU]
Yeah, got it.
[NANA] What happened?
Are you not feeling well?
[IKUNO]
No, nothing like that.
Alright. I guess I shouldn't
be too surprised,
you have always
been a bit unstable.
We'll run some tests
on you tomorrow.
Pardon, but if I may, is it
possible that the two of us
simply have a
compatibility issue?
A lot of teams go
through this at first.
But don't worry,
it isn't grounds for
splitting you two up.
Is that so?
[HIRO gasps]
[computer beeps]
[ICHIGO]
We have visual on the klaxosaur.
FRANXX spreading out.
We're in position.
Beginning the operation.
[MIKU] Wow, it's smaller
than I thought it'd be.
[KOKORO]
What a relief.
[ICHIGO] Stay alert and just
stick to the plan, alright?
[ICHIGO shouts]
[KOKORO gasps]
[MIKU shouts]
[ZOROME]
Gotcha now!
[KLAXOSAUR A screeches]
Way to go, Zorome!
They won!
[ZERO TWO]
Not yet they haven't.
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO]
What do you mean?
[ZOROME] Ha, ha!
You see what I can do?
[MIKU] Cut it out.
You're embarrassing me here.
[ICHIGO] It's not over!
You've gotta destroy the core!
[ZOROME]
Ugh. Yeah, I know.
For a klaxosaur, this thing
wasn't that big a deal.
[KLAXOSAUR A screeches]
[MIKU, ZOROME shout]
[ICHIGO]
Miku!
[ZOROME gasps]
Miku! Are you okay?
Damn you!
[KLAXOSAUR A screeches]
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ZOROME] Hey, Miku!
Say something! Miku!
[ICHIGO]
Miku. Respond!
[GORO gasps]
There's another one?
Uh... Not just one.
[KOKORO gasps]
Just how many are there?
[ICHIGO]
We've gotta get out of here!
[KOKORO gasps]
Right.
This is bad. They've attracted
a whole swarm of klaxosaurs
by releasing their magma energy.
See what I mean? You should've
sent me right from the start.
[NANA]
We couldn't.
Uh-huh. Just remember that
when they all die out there.
[HIRO gasps] Please, let me and
Zero Two go down to help them!
Not happening.
[HIRO gasps]
[HACHI]
You're not an official stamen.
I can't give you permission
to board a FRANXX.
[ZERO TWO] This is no time to
be a stickler for the rules.
This plantation squad is
about to be wiped out. Again.
Send me out already.
Let me ride with my darling.
You will not be
allowed to sortie.
Well, if Hiro can't do it,
then I guess I'll just
have to go instead.
Mitsuru?
She's not wrong. They're all
gonna die down there
if we don't send in
Strelizia right away.
And at the moment, I'm the
only stamen parasite here.
So that means it's up to me.
Strelizia is no
ordinary FRANXX, Mitsuru.
--If you're not used to it's--
--[MITSURU] I'll be fine.
[MITSURU]
Hiro was able to ride in it.
And if he could handle it,
then there's no way
I won't be able to.
[sighs] Can you ride with him?
[ZERO TWO]
Um, did you not hear me?
I said I want to
ride with my darling.
You feel the same, right?
[HIRO]
Zero Two.
[ZERO TWO]
Hm?
[HIRO]
Go with Mitsuru.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
You want me to ride with him?
[HIRO]
Please.
[ZERO TWO sighs] If that's what
you want, darling, I'll do it.
How selfless of you.
But don't come crying to
me when you regret it.
I'll prove I can
pilot Strelizia.
Better than you did.
[HIRO]
In all honesty,
there may have been a part of me
that hoped she would refuse.
[MIKU grunts]
Hello?
You're... You're alive!
Hey! What the--?
--[alarm blares]
--[ICHIGO gasps]
[ZOROME]
Miku's back from the dead!
[KOKORO]
Thank goodness!
[MIKU]
Gimme a break! I didn't die!
[ICHIGO]
Miku. Are you okay?
[MIKU]
I'm fine!
We won't last much longer.
[HACHI]
Strelizia's on its way.
Can you hold out
until it arrives?
[ICHIGO gasps]
All right! If we can
hang on until then...
[KOKORO]
...we're good!
[ICHIGO] Who is it?
Who's piloting it?
Hey, Ichigo! Stay focused.
[grunts] Why'd she
just get so heavy?
Ichigo!
[ICHIGO gasps]
[MIKU]
Hey! Come on!
[MIKU grunts, shouts]
[MIKU]
What's gotten into you?
We can't stay in here!
Let's make a
break for the center!
[GORO]
We can wait for Strelizia here.
[ALL gasp]
[GORO]
Oh, no.
[FUTOSHI]
We can't handle this many!
[MIKU] Uh, hey, Leader.
What do we do?
[ICHIGO]
If I hadn't let my mind wander
to stupid thoughts
back there,
we wouldn't be in
this mess right now.
And Strelizia could've
made it in time.
[ICHIGO] I'm their leader...
and I've failed.
[ALL]
Strelitzia!
[ICHIGO]
Hiro? Is that you?
[MITSURU]
Get back. All of you.
[ZOROME gasps]
Is that Mitsuru?
[HACHI] All units, evacuate and
let Strelizia handle this.
Roger. Let's move, Ichigo.
[ICHIGO]
Oh, yeah.
[pants]
Awesome! I feel the power!
It's like I can do anything!
Amazing how changing partners
can make such a difference.
I knew the problem wasn't me!
I'm every bit as
good as Hiro is!
Hiro! Are you watching?
We're in perfect sync!
I can pilot Strelizia with ease.
And do it without
losing consciousness!
If you want, Zero Two,
I wouldn't mind becoming
your official partner.
Don't you think we'd be
the greatest duo ever?
[ZERO TWO]
Really? You mean that?
Then... I guess I can try
going all-out for a bit.
[gasps]
[HACHI]
Strelizia, that's enough.
The other units have
all evacuated. Now get out--
[ZERO TWO] Nah, I'm gonna
have some fun before I leave.
Stop it! Get back
here right now!
[computer beeps]
That girl...
Prepare to recover Strelizia
and its stamen at once.
On the double.
[IKUNO gasps]
"Recover"?
[KOKORO] Looks like
Strelizia saved us all again.
Never expected
Mitsuru to pilot it.
I'm sorry. That was my bad.
Eh. Doesn't matter
whose fault it was.
We're partners, so we're
in this together.
Miku. Thanks!
What's the matter?
You're not yourself.
[ICHIGO]
Sorry.
I guess I let my guard
down once I heard that
help was on the way.
[ICHIGO]
Get it together!
[FUTOSHI]
Hey. They're back.
[ALL gasp]
[HIRO]
The hand she held out
and the smile she offered
to me alone came at a price.
[HIRO chuckles]
[gasps]
Mitsuru...
[HIRO]
The rumors were true.
Mitsuru's wretched state
was all the proof I needed.
[ZERO TWO]
Yeah, turns out this kid
really isn't cut out
to be my darling.
Only you are my darling.
You alone.
[HIRO] And I thought back
to what she said before.
"I can get you out of here."
♪