[rumbling]
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] Approximate
distance to klaxosaur group,
4,000. ETA is still
zero-two-one-zero hours...
It looks like they're
moving in a pack,
which means that huge thing
could be a klaxosaur as well.
If so, it's unlike any
I've ever seen before.
[ICHIGO grunts]
Are you really going to fight?
I am.
[GORO]
What a fool.
[KOKORO]
Did you hear the numbers?
They're higher than
they estimated.
Do you think we'll be able to
stop them and still make it
back here alive?
All I know is it'll
be unlike anything
we've experienced before.
Don't worry about it, we can
let Squad 26 handle them alone.
You know, since we're just
"deadweight," apparently.
[IKUNO] It's not like
you to pass up a fight.
Given their big
advantage in numbers,
I don't see much reason
for us to be optimistic.
Hey, don't go whimping out.
They may have the numbers,
but you've got Zorome
the Great on your side.
And while he's busy
getting in trouble,
Strelizia will be there
to clean up the mess.
Point is, we won't let
Squad 26 hog the glory.
[MITSURU] Are you fighting
them or the klaxosaurs?
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
Where's Hiro?
He's still inside.
You should probably talk
to him while you can.
[ICHIGO grunts]
[GORO]
Go.
[ICHIGO]
Ah, wha--?
[HIRO]
Ichigo?
[ICHIGO gasps]
Hey, so...
...this operation's starting
pretty late tonight, isn't it?
You well-rested? You can't be
falling asleep halfway through.
I tried, but I was wide awake.
I see.
Well, to be honest, I didn't
really sleep much, either.
[ICHIGO chuckles nervously]
But I took a bath
and felt a bit better.
Good.
[ICHIGO]
Anyway...
Ichigo?
[gasps] Yeah, what?
Let's do what we can to make
sure tonight is a success.
Oh. Of course. Let's do that.
Being a leader's not easy.
I know that.
But I also know you're
more than up to the task.
I'm counting on you.
Totally. Just like how
I'll be counting on you
during this operation, too.
Y'know... because...
Hiro, what I mean to say is.
I've always thought...
Sorry about that.
What've you always thought?
[ICHIGO]
I, uh...
[HIRO grnuts]
I just wanted to tell you...
that I've always thought of you
like you were my sibling.
Yeah. I feel the same way.
And I'm sure Goro does, too.
[ICHIGO exhales]
Ichigo, do your best
as our leader, all right?
Together with Goro!
How did it go?
Hiro sends his regards.
That guy...
[ICHIGO]
Goro. Here's the plan:
We're saving Strelizia
for as late as possible.
[gasps] Understood.
Well, are you ready, darling?
[HIRO grunts]
[MALE OPERATOR A]
Open force gate. Repeat.
Open force gate.
Open force gate, on the double.
Force gate open.
Crimping boosters decompressing.
[FEMALE OPERATOR B]
...I repeat...
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
All FRANXX good to go.
Code Beta's alt mode
still unconfirmed.
[radio chatter]
[MALE OPERATOR B]
Amending enemy's approach route.
Estimated contact
point unchanged.
[MALE OPERATOR D]
Safety systems all green.
[HACHI] We have updated
intel on the klaxosaurs.
Aside from the
Conrad-class pack,
we've also detected
a very dense unit.
[HACHI] It doesn't match
anything we have on record,
but due to its
independent movement,
we've deemed it a klaxosaur
and given it the code name
"Target Beta."
It's huge!
What the heck is that?
[MIKU] And look how many
small ones there are.
[HACHI] It would be reckless
to attack Target Beta
without any information.
Therefore, prioritize
the Conrad-class pack
as soon as you engage.
Code Zero-Nine-Zero
will have field command.
Yes, sir.
It's time.
All FRANXX, commence op.
Strelizia, you stay
where you are.
[SQUAD 13 PILOTS]
Roger!
[CODE 090]
Squad 26, let's go!
[SQUAD 26 PILOTS]
Right!
Remember, everyone,
we have to be thorough.
Keep a level head and
we'll win this thing.
[CODE 090]
How many got past us?
[MALE SQUAD 26 PILOT G]
Three. No, four!
Squad 13, they're yours!
But be careful not to
stray too far ahead.
If you move around haphazardly,
you could impede
our coordination.
If you think we'd hold you back,
just come out and
say so, damn it.
I can't believe he finds
us such a liability.
It's the truth, though.
We're green as hell,
so Squad 26 has to carry us
on their backs, like babies.
What did you say?
They're here!
[KOKORO]
We have to stop them!
[FUTOSHI]
Hold still, damn you!
[KOKORO yelps]
[IKUNO shouts]
[MIKU yells]
[IKUNO gasps]
[MIKU grunts]
Hey, what're you doing?
I put too much
into that, okay?
[MIKU, KOKORO grunt]
[FUTOSHI]
Get your damn claws off Kokoro!
[KOKORO grunts]
[roars]
[KOKORO gasps]
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
Shake it off.
[KOKORO]
Thank you, Ichigo.
[ICHIGO] Zorome, go keep them
busy without getting too close!
You have the speed for it!
[ZOROME]
Tell me something I don't know.
[ICHIGO] Mitsuru! Get over
here and back up Genista!
Easy. Don't get worked up.
Zero-One-Five is skilled.
And her number's in the teens.
Why does a makeshift
team like theirs
have both her and Zero-One-Six?
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Second wave approaching!
[CODE 090] Here they come!
Don't let them through!
[HIRO pants]
[ZERO TWO]
Darling, look.
Your squad mates' tactics
are all over the place.
A huge contrast to the
precision of the other squad.
You're saying they're
being pushed back?
More like they're barely
hanging in there.
Man, I'm starting
to get the itch.
I can't wait for us to
join in on the action.
Hey, Zero Two? Why do
you fight the klaxosaurs?
You always look like
you're enjoying yourself,
so I was wondering if
you have a reason.
[ZERO TWO]
"A reason"?
Maybe because I'm a monster.
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO]
How 'bout you?
[HIRO]
Oh, uh...
I guess, to protect Papa and all
the adults in the plantations.
[ZERO TWO]
That's it?
[HIRO]
Yeah, that's it.
After all, that's our
entire purpose in life.
[ZERO TWO]
Huh. How lame.
If they're in trouble,
we should move out.
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
[MIKU]
What the--? Strelizia?
[ICHIGO gasps]
[GORO gasps]
[CODE 090]
Tch. Of course she's here.
What're you doing? Your orders
were to remain on standby.
Don't worry, I'm just
gonna help my squadmates.
You can't do whatever
the hell you want!
[MALE SQUAD 26 PILOT G]
What now?
Just ignore them.
Let's take these down.
That was cool!
[ZOROME scoffs]
They have some teamwork.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[HIRO pants]
[ZERO TWO]
Darling. Are you done?
[HIRO grunts]
[ZERO TWO]
That's better. Come on!
[ZERO TWO shouts]
[ICHIGO shouts]
[ICHIGO]
Strelizia, go back!
No, it's fine.
We can still fight!
Shut up and get
back to your post!
[ZERO TWO]
So bossy.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Target Beta has breached
the second defense line.
[HACHI] Doesn't look like
it's planning to stop.
[CODE 090] We're going to
attack Target Beta now.
[HACHI]
Be careful.
[ICHIGO]
How's it going to attack?
It's just a cube,
it doesn't have any limbs.
[CODE 090]
Good. It's working. Now!
[ALL shout]
What's that noise?
It's coming from that thing!
[ICHIGO]
Guys, look!
[ALL shout]
[FUTOSHI]
A humanoid form?
[GORO]
This can't be happening.
[NANA]
A Gutenberg-class?
This is bad.
We can't let it get closer!
All units, try again!
[FEMALE SQUAD 26 PILOTS shout]
[CODE 090]
Crap. Everyone fall back!
[CODE 090 gasps]
We're out of fuel?
[gasps]
[ZOROME]
Quit spacing out!
You owe me one, pal!
[CODE 090]
Thanks.
[HACHI]
All Squad 26 units fall back.
Squad 13 will handle
the Gutenberg-class.
[IKUNO]
Easier said than done.
[KOKORO] How are we supposed
to stop something so massive?
Don't think of stopping it,
think of killing it.
If it breaches the wall,
then it's all over for us.
We can handle it if we
team up with Strelizia.
[MIKU] Yeah. That seems
like our only choice.
It doesn't matter
how we do it.
We just gotta show
everyone that our squad
can take care of
business on its own!
I'm in. You can count on us.
[ICHIGO]
Negative!
Strelizia, hold position
where you are.
Huh?
[KOKORO gasps]
There's no way we can
win without them!
[IKUNO] Unless you have some
sort of plan in mind, Ichigo.
[ICHIGO] We'll save Strelizia
for the final blow.
This isn't the
time to hold back!
Calm down, Zorome.
Strelizia's spear is the only
weapon we have that can reach
that thing's core.
[ICHIGO]
Goro.
The plan is for all of
us to create an opening
for Strelizia to strike.
Isn't that right, Ichigo?
[ICHIGO]
Yeah. Right. That's it.
Let's show 'em what
Squad 13 is made of!
Yeah, okay. I guess
that all makes sense.
Did you get all that, Hiro?
We need you to finish it off.
[HIRO] Copy that!
[ICHIGO]
Squad 13, let's move out!
Thank you for that, Goro.
Focus on the task at hand.
[ICHIGO]
'Kay.
[ZOROME]
All right! Here we go!
[ZOROME grunts]
[MIKU]
Stay with it! Be a man!
[ZOROME]
You gotta try, too!
[MIKU]
Of course I do!
I'm not letting anyone
call me deadweight again!
[FUTOSHI grunts]
[KOKORO]
Futoshi!
[IKUNO] We have to set things
up for Strelizia, Mitsuru!
[KOKORO]
Thanks, guys.
Don't have to tell me!
[ZERO TWO]
I know it hurts, darling.
But this won't end until we kill
that thing. Can you do it?
Uh-huh. Course I can.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro!
[GORO]
Now!
[HIRO]
This is the final strike!
[HIRO shouts]
Get in there!
[HIRO pants, gasps]
[HIRO]
We did it...
[ICHIGO]
Hiro!
Run away! Hiro!
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] The link
between Codes Zero-Zero-Two
and Zero-One-Six has broken.
Oh, please, no!
Of all the moments
for time to run out,
why'd it have to be now?
No! Hiro! Zero Two!
Come in! Hiro!
[ICHIGO whimpers]
H-He's dead. Hiro's dead.
Ichigo! Get it together!
[ZOROME]
Hey, Hiro! What are you doing?
[MIKU]
No way.
[IKUNO]
The rumors were really true?
[KOKORO]
We've gotta help them, fast!
[MITSURU] There's no time.
Target Beta's gonna break
through the wall if we
don't do something!
[FUTOSHI]
W-We gotta stop it!
[ICHIGO] I could've saved him.
If I'd told him not to pilot.
That is enough of that!
This is no time to be crying!
We have to save our
own lives right now!
[HIRO]
Huh... I died.
Well, at least I did
everything I could, right?
There you go again,
feeling satisfied with giving
up like you always do.
You aren't even trying
to listen to your partner.
[HIRO]
I didn't give up.
This is just as
far as I could go.
It's not like when
you and I separated.
Besides, I'm sure Zero Two
can keep fighting without me.
That's how she's always fought.
And you're okay with that?
[HIRO] I piloted a Franxx
to the very end.
I got to be of use to everyone.
I have no regrets.
[NAOMI]
Liar.
[HIRO gasps]
Where is this?
[HIRO] Zero Two... You came
to say goodbye to me?
I found a place for myself.
And it's all thanks
to you that I did.
I belonged as a child again.
If only for a bit.
[HIRO gasps]
Hey, wait.
Why do you look so sad?
[ZERO TWO yells]
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO grunts]
What?
[chokes]
[HIRO]
Wait, we didn't kill it? Oh, no.
[ZERO TWO shouts]
[ZERO TWO] You. You're
nothing but a monster!
[HIRO] Zero Two, stop!
You can't do this alone!
If you keep this up,
even you will die!
What reason do you
have to fight so hard?
[ZERO TWO] Reason?
Maybe because I'm a monster.
[HIRO] Is this how it's
always been for you?
You lose your partner
and fight on alone?
Can you not fly
by yourself, either?
You need someone, too?
[ZERO TWO] I'm always alone,
thanks to these horns.
[HIRO]
What the hell is wrong with me?
Zero Two's suffering
and I'm doing nothing!
I want to help you.
I want to ride with
you in Strelizia again.
My wings... exist for you!
[ZERO TWO gasps, shouts]
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Dar... ling?
I'm your partner, Zero Two.
I won't leave you all alone.
[ALL gasp]
Wait. Hiro's... still alive?
[ICHIGO]
Hiro.
[NANA] Hiro's vital signs
are all reading normal.
What's going on?
[FRANXX]
Oh?
[NANA gasps]
Doctor?
[KOKORO]
It's changing forms again!
[MITSURU]
We can't let it!
[MIKU]
Don't just stand there, Ichigo!
Come on!
[IKUNO]
Now's our chance!
[FUTOSHI]
It's our turn!
[ZOROME]
Let's give 'em a hand!
[GORO] Create another
opening for Strelizia!
[ICHIGO]
Right!
Hiro! Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO]
Let's fly...
Yeah!
[ZERO TWO] ...with the
wings I share with you!
With the wings
I share with you!
[ZERO TWO, HIRO shout]
Those were wings.
[FRANXX]
That boy.
He might just make
Zero Two's wish come true.
[HIRO]
Zero Two?
[ZERO TWO]
Mm?
[HIRO] I found another
reason for why I fight.
Why I pilot a Franxx.
[ZERO TWO]
Really? What is it?
Because I want to be your wings.
Though, I don't know what'll
happen to me next time.
You'll be fine. Next and every
other time, my darling.
[HIRO] The Jian, also known as
"the bird that shares wings",
only possesses one wing.
When a male and female lean
on each other and act as one,
they can fly as high and
as far as they want.
[HIRO] If I can be your wings,
then even if my life burns out,
I'll keep leaning
on you, right here.
[HIRO] Because, that may
be my purpose in life.
[ZERO TWO] There are still so
many klaxosaurs I have to kill.
[9'a]
Well, well.
You're certainly hitting it off,
aren't you, Nine Iota?