[HIRO] The place where I came
from doesn't matter to me.
All I care about is living
every moment to its fullest.
[MIKU] Hey, where is it?
I don't see anything at all.
[IKUNO]
Are you sure you saw it?
[GORO]
Yeah, definitely.
[HIRO] That's the defining
feature of being human.
[ZERO TWO]
No picture books. Knew it.
[HIRO] Zero Two feels the
same way. Or so I thought.
I see it! Over there!
[ICHIGO]
Goro was right. That's...
[HIRO]
Yeah. The Garden.
♪
[HIRO] This is the Garden,
the place where we grew up.
It's a parasite
development facility,
where hundreds upon
hundreds of children live.
There's a research hub that
towers over the Garden
and looks down upon it.
We call that "The Lab."
[MIKU] I saw the Lab
everyday from afar,
but I've never been inside.
[KOKORO]
Well, very, very few children
actually get to
come here, right?
[FUTOSHI] I think
Hiro came a few times.
[HIRO]
You're right,
back then I was a designated
special research subject.
[ZOROME]
Pfft. Teacher's pet.
[FUTOSHI]
And Mitsuru did, too, I guess.
Wait. He did?
[MITSURU grunts]
Listen up.
The reason we came back here
is to run tests on all of you.
Sorry to say, this won't
be a homecoming.
You are hereby banned
from entering the Garden.
What kind of tests?
And why do they need to be
done here, of all places?
Well. I think we're
just tagging along.
[GORO, ICHIGO gasp]
[HACHI] Code Zero-Zero-Two, you
will undergo thorough testing.
I think I'll pass.
[NANA] This an order.
We can't put it off any longer.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[9'a]
Oh, hey!
If it isn't Nine Iota.
Quite the coincidence
running into you here.
[9'a shuckles]
But then, maybe not.
You're here for
maintenance, too, right?
I'm glad to see you
haven't changed.
Who is this boy?
Beats me. But what I can
tell you is he's kinda hot!
[ZOROME]
Hm?
Children, these are the Nines.
A special forces unit under APE.
Nice to meet you. You're in the
same squad as Iota, correct?
Then, please escort her to
you-know-where, safe-and-sound.
"You-know-where"?
All of the plantations on
this continent are currently
headed to one location.
Surely they've told you by now.
[ICHIGO]
Uh?
[NANA]
I'll fill you in later.
'Kay.
[9'a] Anyway. It looks like
Iota's fitting in quite nicely
with you guys. That's a relief.
Iota. Do you mean, Zero Two?
Ah, we meet again.
You're correct.
A while ago, that girl was
counted amongst us Nines.
That so? Interesting.
Although. I thought she'd
be a little too much for
ordinary parasites to handle.
You've surprised me.
You must tell me sometime
how you managed to tame her.
[HIRO] What do you
mean by "tame her"?
[ICHIGO] All that matters is
that she's one of us now.
Oh, wow. She must've taken
a real liking to you then.
I never thought she would
buddy up to humans.
And I see that the special
forces haven't been taught
basic etiquette. It makes me
glad that I fight alongside
Zero Two rather than any of you.
[9'a laughs]
All right, I understand.
You guys are a bit different
from the parasites
in the other squads,
aren't you?
That would explain why Iota's
with you in the first place.
[gasps]
--Wha--?
--Hey!
Okay, kids. It's time to go.
I've taken an interest in you,
too. If you would have me,
I'd love to be a part of
your squad sometime.
Sadly, the only room we
have left is the attic,
which doesn't suit an
elite like yourself.
But if that's okay,
you're always welcome.
My, my. So proud and dignified.
[thud]
[HIRO] Zero Two, did something
happen recently?
Instead of dealing with it
alone, why not talk to me?
After all, I'm your partner.
[ZERO TWO]
Then kiss me.
[HIRO]
Huh?
Kiss me.
[HIRO]
Okay...
[HIRO gasps]
Zero Two--
[ZERO TWO]
Never mind.
[GORO] I'm done. You were
right about tagging along.
The tests were all really basic.
[ZERO TWO]
I said don't touch me!
Get away from me!
[HIRO] I'm thinking about
going to the Garden after this.
What? We're forbidden
from going there.
Now that I found
myself a partner,
I wanna see Naomi
and let her know.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Damn you!
Don't cause me any
more trouble, Zero Two.
[HIRO] You guys didn't
have to come along.
[KOKORO gasps]
Sorry about that, Futoshi.
[FUTOSHI chuckles]
[ZOROME] It wouldn't've been
fair for you to sneak out
all by yourself.
Yeah, and since
we're already here,
it'd be dumb for
us to go back now.
[HIRO] So, have you
finished reading this?
Yeah, I finished it, but I
didn't understand it at all.
[HIRO chuckles] Same here.
Although, I did take away
the part in this book
about the "holy tree."
Wait, what holy tree?
Apparently, it's a reference
to the mistletoe.
I hear there's one
in the Garden, too.
I hope I get to see it, someday.
[GORO]
So weird to think about.
It hasn't even been six
months since we left.
And yet, it feels like
the distant past.
[door hisses]
Come with me.
[ALL gasp]
[ZOROME] Wait. Hold on.
We were never like this, right?
Uh, I don't think that we were.
[GORO gasps]
See that?
It's the same type of injection
they administered to us.
But they're so young,
and they're already getting
parasite injections?
[FEMALE NURSE A]
Indeed.
We've started giving more
concentrated doses of
yellow blood cells
than in the past.
I'm sure you're aware the
klaxosaurs have grown
more active lately.
As a result, the system is being
retooled to produce more
capable and obedient parasites.
Speaking of, you're the
parasites from Squad 13, yes?
You're not supposed
to be in here.
Um, ma'am. Has a girl from our
plantation called "Naomi"--
Has Code Seven-Zero-Three
been back here yet?
[FEMALE NURSE 12A]
Code Seven-Zero- Three?
Of course not. Once a
parasite leaves the Garden,
they never return to it again.
[IKUNO] I had a feeling
that'd be the case.
[ZOROME] Can't believe
they threw us out!
[MIKU]
...then where is she?
[HIRO] Thinking back,
that's how it always was.
I remember one day at this
facility, when several children
who lived with us,
vanished without a trace.
We asked the adults about it,
but they wouldn't
tell us a thing.
So I eventually
came to realize...
[HIRO]
...that none of us children,
would ever become adults.
A mistletoe.
This really is the place.
But have I already
been here before?
[GORO] Why did Hiro tell us
to head back without him?
I wonder where he's
running off to this time.
[ICHIGO]
Who knows?
[KOKORO] Where do you
guys think we came from?
[ZOROME]
Huh?
Where'd that question
come from?
Obviously, Papa and the
other adults made us.
Is that really
the truth, though?
[ALL sigh]
[ZOROME] Kokoro,
you're acting kinda weird.
[NANA]
There you are!
I've never seen
children disobey orders
and get yelled at
like that before.
You and your squad
truly are interesting.
Can't you go bother
someone else?
[9'a] How cold. The Nines and
I are going to be leaving soon,
so what's a little
chat going to hurt?
[9'a] I hear you guys are
actually a test team.
One formed by Dr. Franxx.
Is that why they give you
so much more freedom
than the squads from
the other plantations?
Just what kind of tests
do they have you doing?
I'd love to hear the details.
Only one of Iota's partners
has ridden with her more than
three times, and that's
Code Zero-One-Six.
Could that, perhaps,
be related to your tests?
What are you trying to say?
Ah, you finally looked
my way. If you want,
I can let you in
on a big secret.
I'll tell you what
Code-Zero-Zero Two
is really like.
[ICHIGO gasps]
She can never co-exist with you
and your other squad members.
Right now, she's merely
wearing a human disguise
and pretending that she can.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[HACHI]
Five Moho-class.
They aren't much
of a threat, but...
[NANA]
Why have they shown up here?
That's the real question.
Seeing as no klaxosaur
has ever been sighted
in this area before.
Is it possible they've become
aware of what we're up to?
[HACHI]
All FRANXX, prepare to sortie.
[HIRO]
Sorry. I'm here!
[HIRO gasps]
Zero Two, your horns.
Quit staring already.
Oh... Sorry.
[ZERO TWO]
Darling?
Let's kill a whole lot of
klaxosaurs again today.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[ZERO TWO]
Huh?
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Hold on!
[ICHIGO] Strelizia! Make sure
you follow the plan!
[HIRO]
Yeah, you're being too direct!
[ZERO TWO]
Oh, shut up!
As long as we kill them all,
what difference does it make?
Hiro, check your four o'clock!
[HIRO]
Damn it.
Zero Two! Pay attention!
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Why, you...!
You're chasing them too far!
We have to work with the others!
[KOKORO]
They're fast!
[IKUNO] Strelizia!
There's more coming your way!
[ZERO TWO]
I'll crush them all at once!
Why aren't you listening
to me? Zero Two!
Damn!
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Darling!
Why are you getting
in my way now, too?!
[HIRO]
Fire!
[HIRO panting]
Not sure how, but we got 'em.
[ZERO TWO]
You damn monsters.
Take this. And this!
Zero Two! That's enough!
You don't need to
hit them, anymore!
[ZERO TWO] Damn you! I'm going
to kill every single one of you!
And become human.
We're out of power.
[IKUNO] I think you
went a bit overboard.
[MIKU]
That was kinda scary.
[ICHIGO]
Uh...
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO]
Zero Two.
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO]
Your nails are peeling off!
And you're covered in bruises.
[ZERO TWO]
Let go.
Kill them.
[HIRO]
What?
I don't have much time.
I need to kill more.
So many more klaxosaurs.
I wanna hurry up
and become human.
You mentioned that earlier.
What did you mean?
[ZERO TWO] I'm going
to be human... Human.
[HIRO]
Snap out of it, Zero Two!
I have no idea why you're
so fixated on being human,
but you are who you are!
How you were born
doesn't matter!
And neither do your
horns and fangs!
[ZERO TWO]
Shut your damn mouth!
[HIRO] I was attracted
to the person you are!
It doesn't matter
whether you're human!
This entire time, I've been
trying to figure out why
I felt this way about you.
And after watching Goro
and Futoshi, I understand.
I know what this feeling is!
Zero Two, I love you! I love you
exactly the way that you are!
"Love me"? What's that mean?
[HIRO grunts]
[HIRO]
What are you--?
[ZERO TWO] Is this it? It's what
you're talking about, right?
Then I'll teach you what
comes after kissing.
[HIRO]
No, that's not it--
[HIRO gasps] Stop that!
This isn't what I meant!
You're wrong. I was...
This is so tedious.
Just hurry up and let it out.
But this isn't enough.
You still have to kill more
of those monsters
and make me human!
After all, you're nothing
more than my fodder!
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO]
Fodder?
[HACHI] The detailed testing
shows that Code Zero-Zero-Two's
rate of saurification
has accelerated
since they became partners.
And Code Zero-One-Six's
numbers are nearing
the upper limit as well.
If this keeps up,
he could very well undergo
a genetic transformation.
[NANA] Are you saying
that he would no longer
be considered human?
[water trickling]
[ZERO TWO breathes heavily]
Hey, could I talk
to you for a se--
[glass shatters]
[ZERO TWO] Don't show me...
Don't reflect me!
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Zero Two, what're you doing?
[ICHIGO gasps]
[gasps]
[9'a] Why do you think it is
that Iota came to be known
as "the Partner Killer"?
Because she curses her partners.
It's how she drains
their lives away.
That power is what she
uses to pilot the FRANXX.
And she can do that
because Iota's the key
to saving the world.
What are you saying?
This makes no sense.
She's used and discarded
more than a hundred stamens.
And I'm only counting
the ones I'm aware of.
Code Zero-One-Six is
an exceptional case.
Maybe he has a special ability
that keeps him going.
However, if he continues
to ride with her,
then the curse might turn
him into the same kind of
monster that she is.
She must believe that the
more klaxosaurs she kills,
the closer she gets
to being human.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro!
[ZERO TWO shouts]
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
Strelizia!
[ZERO TWO growls]
Move it!
I'll kill many, many more,
and then I'll become a human!
No, you're wrong!
[ZERO TWO grunts]
That is no way for
you to become human!
What is driving this
obsession of yours?
[ZERO TWO]
Don't you dare!
I'm not gonna let
you tie me down!
Now shut up and let
yourself be devoured like
the fodder that you are!
[ZERO TWO yells]
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[HIRO]
Stop!
[gasps]
[HIRO]
Zero Two...
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO]
Give me all of your life.
I'm going to become human.
So I can finally meet my
darling from back then.
Dar... ling?
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Para-capacity has crossed
critical point and
is still rising.
[NANA] This is bad.
The saurification will begin!
[HIRO]
What's going on?
Someone's thoughts are
flowing into my mind.
[HIRO] I don't know when it was,
but I've seen all this before.
[HIRO]
Hands clasped together,
eyes filled with
hatred for the world.
A girl with red skin
and blue blood.
[HIRO gasps] I remember.
That girl... She's...
[ZERO TWO] That's right.
I'm a monster in disguise.
♪