[ZERO TWO]
We've left on our honeymoon,
heading to the ends
of the universe.
The road there is all too long.
Even so...
[HIRO]
It's strange.
So many days have passed,
but I haven't been feeling
hungry or sleepy at all.
Will I turn... completely
into a klaxosaur?
[ZERO TWO]
Are you scared?
No way.
It's almost like I've
become a part of you.
And I'm going deeper
and deeper in.
I can tell what you're feeling.
Same for me, darling.
[ZERO TWO]
More enemies.
[HIRO]
Zero Two, let's do this.
Come to me, darling.
[HIRO]
When we share our wings,
we can fly as high
and as far as we want.
Right now,
we are unbreakable.
[007]
It's getting a bit big.
I'll arrange pregnancy
clothes for you.
If you could.
No. Please.
I don't want to be given any
kind of special treatment.
I must.
As the first pregnancy,
you'll be a pioneer
and an example for others.
We should do things right
to set forth a precedent.
[KOKORO]
Hm. 'Kay.
[ZOROME]
And here we go!
Ah! We found the place!
[ICHIGO]
I'm amazed it's still here.
Don't try to explore
any unsafe areas!
[GROUP]
Okay.
[FUTOSHI]
Unreal.
The plants were dying
back then, but now...
It's like a miracle.
[ZOROME] We went through
so much here, didn't we?
Maybe Mistilteinn kept
all of this safe for us
so we'd return.
Maybe. This is our chance.
We can make a fresh start now.
All right!
[ICHIGO] What do you need
all these files for?
Well, because there's
something I wanna get done.
You're so good at that!
Take the thread,
and then you...
[MITSURU]
Um...
Is there anything that
you need me to do for you?
You shouldn't worry so much.
Everybody's here for me.
I'll be fine.
[MITSURU]
But I feel like I should help.
[ZOROME, FUTOSHI]
Kokoro!
[ZOROME]
Outta my way, fatty!
[FUTOSHI]
Don't call me that!
Kokoro, eat this stuff!
Huh?
[ZOROME]
No fair! Eat this, too!
Thank you, you guys.
We asked Nana and she said
we could bring it to you.
You need to eat a bunch and
get all those nutrients!
Yeah. Thanks so much.
[ZOROME] All right.
Back to the field we go.
[MITSURU]
Wait. Hold on a second.
[FUTOSHI] Relax! There's still
time before it's born!
--[MITSURU] Um.
--[KOKORO] Huh?
I... guess I'm off.
'Kay. I'll see ya later.
[ICHIGO] Do you think Hiro and
Zero Two are still fighting?
Honestly, every now and then,
it really hurts to think
about how we're living here
without the two of them.
And I just keep wishing
there was something useful
we could do to help them out.
We feel the exact
same way as you.
But still...
All that's left to focus on
is what we can do here and now.
Just like they're doing.
[ZERO TWO] Can you tell
which stars these are?
[HIRO] Not at all.
We're really far from Earth.
And from this perspective,
they look so different.
[ZERO TWO] Want to make a
constellation ourselves, then?
[HIRO]
Make one?
[ZERO TWO] For example,
we can link those two stars--
[alarm sounds]
[ZERO TWO]
Too bad. The enemy's here.
Let's go, darling.
[HIRO]
Right.
[ZERO TWO]
Don't worry.
We have all the time
in the world.
[MITSURU panting]
--[GORO] Mitsuru! Hurry up!
--[ZOROME] Ah, there he is!
Kokoro!
[gasps]
Lookit, there's your papa.
[ICHIGO] The first step
in the future we chose
finally came to pass.
[FUTOSHI]
Well done, Mitsuru!
You're the first papa!
[ICHIGO] It was something
we'd never forget.
[ZOROME]
You're gonna suffocate him!
[ICHIGO] Some time later, we
were told about the facility.
The one that housed all
the children who disappeared.
Naomi!
You guys...
[ICHIGO] We threw
ourselves into this life,
taking each step
slowly but surely.
[ICHIGO] Making sure we could
each find our own path to walk.
[ICHIGO] And then one of us came
to another major crossroads.
[GORO] Okay, I'm going
to explore the world.
I'll find things we need.
Like useable materials
that'll help in the future.
Also...
I wanna look for any children
that were left behind.
They desperately
need a helping hand.
It'll be a long journey
for you. Good luck.
And take care of yourself.
You okay with this, Ichigo?
We'll all miss him, but...
I am.
'Cause what he's doing
is a very Goro way to live.
Good to go.
All right,
then do your thing.
[GORO] I can't let Hiro
outshine me forever.
[ICHIGO]
Right.
Try to contact us now and then.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[ZOROME, MIKU yelp]
Hey! What was that?
[GORO]
Okay, take care, guys.
And I'll find that thing
you asked about, Ikuno.
Yeah, yeah. Thanks a bunch.
Later!
[IKUNO sighs] Goro's changed
a lot, hasn't he?
[ICHIGO] Through this cycle
of meetings and partings,
we're gradually growing
up and becoming adults.
Hiro. Zero Two.
How are you two doing?
It's just a little bit
lonely without you both.
[ICHIGO] But we're giving
our all to our lives here
so we can face you
with our heads held high.
[ICHIGO] And then, we passed two
years since that fateful day.
[ZERO TWO]
Darling.
Are you okay?
Sorry, guess I fell asleep.
[ZERO TWO]
That's unusual.
You seem to be really weak.
Don't push yourself.
[HIRO]
Thanks, but I'll be fine.
Zero Two. I had a dream.
[ZERO TWO]
A dream?
One about the gang.
They were living good lives.
Yeah...
[ZERO TWO]
Darling.
We're nearing the
enemy's home planet.
[PAPA, APE VICE CHIEF]
You feeble lifeform,
bound to your flesh.
[ZERO TWO]
VIRM!
[PAPA, APE VICE CHIEF]
Heed my voice!
Don't even bother!
My darling won't listen to you--
What?
Is that Hringhorni?
[APE VICE CHIEF]
This is our territory.
[PAPA]
Feeble one.
Let me deliver you
from your suffering.
Darling, let's go!
[ZERO TWO]
Darling?
Darling!
[ZERO TWO] Darling!
Hang in there, darling!
[ZERO TWO shouts]
Why? What's wrong?
Why can't I hear his voice
when he's right here?
[HIRO]
Zero Two?
Zero Two!
You're right here, but your
voice is growing so distant.
[ZERO TWO] What did
you do to my darling?
[PAPA] Gently caressed his
surface consciousness.
That's all.
[APE VICE CHIEF] Every physical
body has its limits,
and he is but a frail human.
You two may have a shallow
connection, but as a pure
klaxosaur crystallization, you
are not a good match for him.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
No!
Stop it!
[HIRO]
It's so quiet.
Where am I going?
I vowed to be with you forever,
so why can't I stand
with you until the end?
Is it because I'm human?
My darling. My darling's
mind is fading away.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[screams]
[ZERO TWO]
Please. I'm begging you.
Guys...
Please save my darling.
[AI]
Huh?
Darling! Darling!
[MITSURU]
What's the matter, Ai?
You know you shouldn't do that.
Papa. Darling!
Is something wrong, Papa?
Well, uh, Kokoro--
[KOKORO sighs] I keep telling
you to call me "Mama."
[MITSURU]
Uh, she's...
Darling!
Huh? What the...?
That's weird, she shouldn't
know that word yet.
Wait a sec, could it be?
We should let everyone know!
[IKUNO] I heard it was
originally yours.
So I wasn't sure whether
to show you or not.
I'm certain I can only
stand here right now
because of whatever role
this mirror played in things.
So I should be grateful.
--[door opens]
--[NAOMI] Uh?
You two, come with me!
[ZOROME] This Zero Two is linked
to the one in outer space?
[MITSURU]
I can't say for sure exactly.
Even so, how are we
supposed to use this one
to talk to the other?
We should all link up, too.
C'mon, guys.
[ICHIGO] And so, we started
praying to the skies.
All day, all night.
More and more people
joined us by the day,
and we all screamed
our throats hoarse
at something that
may not be there.
[ZERO TWO]
I can hear them.
All their voices!
Darling! Can you hear them too?
Listen! We're trying!
We're doing our
best here on Earth!
We haven't forgotten about you!
You hear me?
Not a day goes by we
don't think about you!
Squad 13 doesn't feel complete.
Not without the both of you.
But we've gained
loads of new friends
in the time you've been away!
I'll never let you guys
outshine me! You got that?
I'm gonna take my own path!
That's right!
And we promise we'll all
find our own happiness,
no matter what, okay?
I've decided, whatever
time I have left,
I'm going to make
the most of it!
Hiro!
We had our child
and gave her a name!
Just like you once
gave us all of ours!
[KOKORO] It's Ai, for "love"!
The word we were never taught!
I read an old book
and learned about bonds
like the one you two have.
It means that you
love each other.
We want our child, our Ai,
to inherit that bond!
That's what we decided!
[HIRO]
I hear... their voices.
Ai.
[ZERO TWO]
That's right. Humans are strong.
[HIRO]
Zero Two?
[ZERO TWO]
This is something you started.
You've always yelled out
that you want to be there
and live together with everyone.
[HIRO] It's not something
to be proud of.
Mine was a petty, selfish wish.
I thoughtlessly rushed
toward everything,
and I caused trouble
for everyone.
[ZERO TWO] But that's how badly
you wanted to live, right?
That's why you yelled to me that
you wanted to be here, right?
You dazzled me.
Your pained expression
and your tears,
they were exactly the
humanity I always wanted.
And so, we were bound by a kiss.
A symbol saying
"You're mine and mine alone.
You're special to me."
We met by chance
and were attracted to
each other by nature.
Now, say my name, darling!
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
It's time to become one!
We are the Jian!
I feel your blood.
I feel it coursing
through my veins!
You're dyeing every
part of me in your colors!
I was so blessed
to have met you all!
I'm glad I was born
into this world!
Darling! I love you!
Same here.
Zero Two! I love you!
[ZERO TWO, HIRO yell]
[HIRO]
Commence implanting!
What?
[ZERO TWO yelps]
Not yet.
We've gotta rewrite that story
and continue it together!
Zero Two. I am
becoming one with you.
Now you are me.
And you are me.
So, we're probably going
to disappear soon.
But still, the path we've
walked on won't ever fade.
The others will take it further.
It doesn't matter how long.
If we have souls, then I
swear I'll meet you again.
Back where we started.
Back on Earth.
[HIRO]
I love you, Zero Two.
[ZERO TWO]
I feel the same.
I love you, darling.
[PAPA]
All of you so-called souls,
are you going back to be
caged in your bodies?
[APE VICE CHIEF]
You willingly choose
to be shackled by
pain and sorrow?
[PAPA]
VIRM will not die.
[APE VICE CHIEF] I'm sure
we will face off once again
at the apex of evolution.
[PAPA, APE VICE CHIEF]
So long as this universe
contains a flicker of life.
[GORO]
It's over, huh?
All the prayers
that we were saying.
Do you think they
managed to reach them?
I'm sure they did. They heard.
[KOKORO]
Thanks to Hiro and Zero Two,
this planet can go back and
start over from square one.
[AI]
Mama?
[ICHIGO]
Take as long as you want,
but make sure you
both come back here.
We'll keep our home
up and running,
so you can return anytime.
What the...?
[ICHIGO] That bright light shone
upon us for three days straight.
And a few days later, many
klaxosaurs returned to Earth
from the battle,
dove straight into the ground,
and became a part of it.
[ICHIGO]
Hachi said that...
...maybe they decided to
let mankind have Earth.
And then, eight years passed.
[KOKORO] As we decided to
rebuild our lives on Earth,
we made a vow.
[ZOROME]
A vow to stop using
what little magma
energy we had left.
[FUTOSHI] Because it's a symbol
of the klaxosaurs' bonds,
and something very precious
to the planet itself.
[MITSURU] But that decision
brought our lives
adversity after adversity.
[GORO] Because we had to conjure
up a self-sufficient lifestyle
out of thin air.
[IKUNO] Using our meager food
reserves as a foundation...
[MIKU] ...we gradually
made everything.
All that we needed to live.
[ICHIGO] And then, we finished
the rest of that picture book.
So that those two would
forever be as one.
And future generations
would know about them.
[ICHIGO laughs]
[ICHIGO]
Man, you suck.
[NANA]
What do you think?
Is there anything
we can do for them?
We never grow any older,
and we're stuck in the middle,
neither adults nor children.
We have only
a single obligation.
To reach out to
humanity's future
and continue to watch over it.
Wow. You're always
so unyielding.
Well, I don't have
any emotions,
but that's why you're here.
If you were to stay
by my side forever,
I wonder if I would
also be able to change.
[NANA gasps]
[GIRL A]
Hey, hey, Hachi!
Come play with us!
[HACHI]
Oh. Sure. I'll be right back.
[NANA chuckles]
You don't have to worry.
You have changed
and so have I.
And we will all
continue to change.
[ZOROME] Phew! Looking at
this really drives home
how many pipsqueaks
we have now.
[GIRL B]
Mr. Zorome!
Huh?
[GIRL B] Ms. Nana was
mad that you skipped the
teachers' meeting.
[GIRL C]
Totally mad!
It's fine.
I don't have to attend
those stupid meetings.
But bad girls need
to be punished!
Take that!
[GIRL B, GIRL C, ZOROME laugh]
[MIKU]
Hey!
[ZOROME grumbles]
[ZOROME]
Oh, Miku.
Why don't you quit
slacking for a change
and help us out over here?
Shaddup! I was just
about to get started!
Oh?
Because it sure didn't
look like you were to me!
--[BOTH laughing]
--[ZOROME] Come off it.
[ZOROME]
I'm busy with stuff.
[MIKU]
What stuff exactly?
[ZOROME]
You know, stuff.
[ICHIGO] Sounds like
they're arguing again.
Even on a day when everyone's
supposed to meet up.
Those two are
incapable of changing.
Everything looks good.
It's growing fine.
Thank you, Ikuno.
[IKUNO]
You're going to be a mom.
I wonder what your
baby will be like.
--[door opens]
--[FUTOSHI] I'm here, Ikuno.
[IKUNO]
Futoshi.
New recipe! You wanna
try this bread?
[NAOMI] You haven't
lost any weight at all.
Oh, back off.
Anyway, it was Ikuno's fault
I regained my appetite.
It's all thanks to
the research you did.
We ex-parasites owe you so much.
You've kept our accelerated
aging in check.
Don't think your bread
isn't special, as well.
All the kids here
grow up eating it.
[FUTOSHI laughs]
Kokoro and Mitsuru,
they're on their fourth.
[IKUNO]
I heard.
Like you're one to talk.
[FUTOSHI]
Huh? Oh.
Go on. We're good here.
Get back to your family.
[FUTOSHI laughs]
All right.
[IKUNO]
Where's Goro?
He should be arriving soon.
[IKUNO] He's still traveling
all over the place.
--But you know what he said?
--[ICHIGO] Hm?
[IKUNO ] He wants to stay put
by your side for a while,
for the baby's sake.
[ICHIGO chuckles]
Yeah.
[ZOROME]
We're all grown up now, huh?
[MIKU]
Your mental age disagrees.
[GORO] Although,
we're nothing like the adults
we grew up watching.
[KOKORO]
Anything goes.
As long as we're good
role models for our kids.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro. Zero Two.
We're all living strong,
with our own lives now.
You two were the ones
who showed us how to...
[FUTOSHI]
...enjoy every experience.
[IKUNO]
Fight when you have to.
[ZOROME]
Keep working towards your goal.
[MIKU] Never half-ass things
and go all-out.
[KOKORO] Try and get to
know another person better.
[MITSURU] Choose your
destiny with your own hands.
[GORO]
Be honest with your feelings.
[ICHIGO]
And be someone's wings.
In that sense,
I know that you two were more
human than anybody else.
[HIRO]
One day, for sure.
[ZERO TWO]
Yeah. One day, for sure.
[WOMAN]
Stop running! You'll fall!
[GIRL]
I'll be fine!
[BOY gasps]
[GIRL]
Ow, ow, ow.
Are you okay?
[GIRL]
Who are you?
[BOY]
Me?
My name is...