[GORO] "No one can swim in
the same river water twice."
[ZOROME grunts]
[GORO] That's an old saying
Hiro told me about.
[ZOROME grunts]
--[ALL gasp]
--[engines roaring]
[GORO]
Everything changes.
All things eventually pass.
And nothing remains stagnant.
Yes. Like a river. That is
the nature of our world.
[GORO] Lately, I often
recall these words
and the fact that no
one can halt the flow.
In this world without Papa,
where we don't need to pilot
the FRANXX--not anymore.
[HIRO]
Say, "Ah."
Come on, Zero Two.
Open your mouth. Please?
You're bleeding!
[gasps]
♪
[IKUNO] Can't we increase
the portions a little bit?
[ICHIGO]
No can do.
We only have food reserves
for around one more year.
But the veggies we
planted in the field
are growing just fine.
Yeah, yeah. And we'll
be able to harvest them
in a couple months when
they're fully grown.
Right, Kokoro?
The fact that you know
so much about plants
is super lucky for us.
Oh, no. I don't really know
anything about harvesting.
[ICHIGO] Right. So we should
maintain the status quo
until we have a firm
estimate for the harvest.
[ZOROME groans]
[GORO] Mitsuru,
how's the energy system?
[MITSURU] We still
haven't serviced the unit
that's been acting up lately.
Output's gone down.
[GORO] Hm... How'd the water
purification system look?
Its efficiency has
dropped as well.
[GORO]
What's wrong?
[FUTOSHI]
I've just been wondering.
Should we really keep
using magma energy?
I mean, it did originally belong
to the klaxosaurs, right?
[ZOROME]
Well, what else can we do?
How else are we gonna live?
It's used in food preservation
and for treating wounds too,
you know.
[FUTOSHI]
I do know, but...
[KOKORO gags]
Sorry. I need to lie down.
[MIKU]
You okay?
[KOKORO]
I'm fine.
How do you feel, Hiro?
About using magma energy.
Uh... Oh.
Look, we're gonna have to
survive any way that we can.
So let's figure out what we
need to make that happen.
[ICHIGO]
Cheer up.
[HIRO gasps]
Ichigo?
Sorry. I guess...
that's impossible.
Given the state
Zero Two is in now.
I've said this before,
but let us know if we
can help in any way.
We're all worried about you two.
Sorry, Ichigo.
[ICHIGO]
Don't apologize, dummy.
[GIRL PARASITE A]
Um, Code Zero-One-Five?
We have a problem.
[ICHIGO]
I heard...
...that you've been refusing
to eat since yesterday.
[9'a sighs]
Eating that stuff...
...can only abate our
condition for so long.
What we really need
is maintenance.
[ICHIGO]
I'll leave your food here.
[9'a grunts]
[9'a]
Damn it!
[007] I understand where
you're coming from.
But unfortunately, I cannot
make any decisions
without Papa's approval.
But if things keep going the way
they are and nothing changes,
we're all eventually
going to die!
Yes, I suppose so.
[GORO gasps]
[ICHIGO]
Thanks.
If the farm ends up working
out and we don't have
to worry about food anymore,
we can finally start looking
ahead and plan for the future.
[GORO] I went and
spoke to the new Nana.
I asked for power and
purification system repairs.
[ICHIGO]
No go?
[GORO]
Yeah.
Life in the outside
world is hard, huh?
You run into obstacles
everywhere. It's like...
[ICHIGO] "No one can swim in
the same river water twice."
It's a saying that Hiro
taught me in the past.
These days, I think
about it often.
[GORO gasps]
I hope they get better soon.
Him and Zero Two.
[ICHIGO]
Mm-hm.
Even more cuts... Why?
[ZOROME grunts]
[IKUNO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
Are you okay?
Don't push yourself.
Thanks for the concern.
But I'm fine now,
because my fever's gone down.
[HIRO]
I'm late. Sorry.
Whoa, dude, you look like
a total wreck today.
You should sit this
one out, Hiro.
It's all right.
No, you really...
[ALL grunt]
[ZOROME] What's going on?
An earthquake?
[gasps] Look!
[ALL gasp]
[HIRO]
Is that a... klaxosaur?
[GORO] No, there's a
VIRM soldier too!
They killed each other!
[KOKORO gags]
Kokoro!
Are you all right?
[KOKORO]
Y-Yes.
Oh, man. You don't think they're
going to attack Earth again?
No. There's no way.
--[engines roaring]
--[ALL gasp]
[FUTOSHI] The klaxosaurs
are flying off again.
[MIKU]
Kokoro! What's wrong with you?
[KOKORO whimpers]
[FUTOSHI]
Kokoro!
[ICHIGO]
Let Nana know!
--[MITSURU] K-Kokoro.
--[MIKU] Hurry!
[IKUNO]
Got it!
Kokoro!
[007]
The results are in.
Her urine sample revealed traces
of human chorionic gonadotropin.
According to the database,
this is a hormone secreted
during pregnancy.
[KOKORO]
"Pregnancy"?
[IKUNO]
And what does that mean?
[007] It is considered
impossible for a pregnant woman
to pilot the FRANXX.
Past records indicate abortion.
That is, the removal
of the fetus
is one of the possible
treatments used.
Please let me know when
you've decided what to do.
[KOKORO gasps]
Wait. Don't leave.
What should I...
Tell me! What should I do!
--[MIKU] Calm down, Kokoro!
--[KOKORO] Tell me!
[ICHIGO]
Boys, give us a moment.
[MITSURU]
What am I supposed to do?
Hiro, what should I do?
Mitsuru, you have--
No, don't.
[HIRO]
I don't know. I have no idea.
What should we do?
What's the right thing to do?
How am I supposed to know that?
[gasps] Zero Two?
Zero Two! Where did you go?
[HIRO]
Wait!
[HIRO gasps]
Zero Two!
[HIRO] Zero Two...
Have you regained your--?
[HIRO gasps]
[GORO]
Guys! Come with me! Right now!
[ZOROME] Come on.
Ya gotta be... kidding me.
They were growing
fine yesterday.
We gave them water
and fertilizer
just like the instructions said.
[engine roars]
[GORO]
Is that?
[ALL gasp]
[IKUNO]
Hachi!
[MIKU]
Nana?
[NANA]
Hey. What is this place?
[HACHI]
I have no idea either.
I'm just following
the doctor's orders.
What's this?
[HACHI]
A database of adults?
All of the memories stored in
their brains have been copied
and archived.
"Cast your bodies aside
and take your minds
to eternal paradise," huh?
Why? Why didn't you
just leave me be?
[NANA]
I don't serve a purpose anymore.
You should've just abandoned me.
[gasps]
[HACHI]
What is that?
[BOTH gasp]
[HACHI]
Could it be?
[NANA gasps]
Naomi?
What's going on?
Why are all the children
who were deemed unfit
and disappeared from the
Garden in these chambers?
After the siege of the
Gran Crevasse was over,
I received an email
from the doctor.
Apparently, it was programmed
to be sent automatically
after his death.
Aside from location data,
it also contained a
message from him.
It said to bring
you here, and...
"You two become the
children's new adults."
And how exactly am I
supposed to do that?
[MIKU]
Hey, Nana!
I'm so glad!
You came back to us!
Please, help... Help us!
[NANA gasps]
[HACHI]
This is only conjecture,
but it's possible the decades
of extracting magma energy
have caused this.
Our mining may have depleted
the very soil itself of life.
[ALL gasp]
Ah! What the heck are
you saying? Nuh-uh.
Like, wouldn't that mean--?
So on top of everything else,
we were rejected again
by the planet itself...
[thud]
[IKUNO]
Ichigo?
[GORO]
Ichigo!
Here. How is she?
[IKUNO]
They say it was overwork.
She worries about
everyone but herself.
Really. What a fool.
[GORO grunts]
[GORO]
Hiro!
Goro?
You heard about
the field, right?
You had to've.
So let's figure it out.
Surely there's a way we can
make it productive again
if we all work together.
Don't you agree?
I found her.
[GORO gasps]
[HIRO]
Zero Two... Not again!
Hey!
You'll catch a cold out here.
Let's go inside, Zero Two.
Come on.
Now, Zero Two.
[HIRO gasps]
You're sure? You'll be
okay by yourself?
[HIRO]
I wanna keep an eye on her.
[MIKU]
Fine.
What happened back there?
Just tell me... Please.
[HIRO sighs]
[HIRO]
Hm?
Huh? Didn't she finish it?
"And so, she turned into a
bird and took to the skies.
Leaving the prince all alone."
[gasps] You knew all along?
You knew that we'd have
to part like them someday.
So you left the
last page for me?
Why would you?
That's just... cruel!
[HIRO gasps]
No way. It can't be.
Are you... Are you up there?
Hold on. Hachi! Zoom in!
On that part there!
[GORO]
Mistilteinn?
I see. So Mistilteinn
is different.
I've heard that it contains
soil from before this planet
became a desert.
Then if we start
planting fields there
and gradually expand them--
[HACHI]
We'll stand a chance.
[GORO gasps] I have to go
and let everyone know!
[HACHI]
Code Zero-One-Six?
[ZOROME]
For real?
Yeah! He said we still
stand a chance.
Yeah! Then let's head back
to Mistilteinn already!
Oh! Hiro.
[ZOROME]
There you are! Late again!
You guys. I need to talk to you.
[ICHIGO]
Huh? You're going to space?
[GORO]
To meet with Zero Two?
What are you saying?
Zero Two is inside her room.
Her body is, but her mind
is inside Strelizia.
As we speak,
she's fighting in space.
Let's slow down.
My brain can't keep up.
How are you gonna get
to space, anyway?
Do you even have a plan?
[HIRO] There's a way. A way
the klaxosaurs left us.
[HACHI] I found it while
looking for cultivable land.
[HACHI] It's a klaxosaur ship,
but for some strange reason,
I could access its
internal systems.
[HIRO grunts]
[001] Decide whether you want
to fight or accept your ruin.
I can take this ship to space?
[HACHI] Probably.
However, this course...
[HIRO gasps]
[ZOROME, FUTOSHI]
Mars orbit?
Isn't that like
stupidly far away?
[HIRO]
Yeah.
Then, will you even be able
to come back afterwards?
[HIRO]
I don't know.
You'll be fighting
those monsters!
[HIRO]
That's right.
We're saying you could
lose your life if you go.
[HIRO]
I know.
I know that it's reckless,
but if I don't take
the risk and act now,
I will never be able
to forgive myself.
So I'm going.
I just wanted to let
you guys know. Goodbye.
[ZOROME gasps]
Hey, wait.
[GORO grunts]
[GORO]
Hold it!
Why, Hiro? We need
to work together.
We have to start over
again from scratch here.
So why do you have to
do this right now?
It's Zero Two.
I can't leave her alone.
We made a promise.
Even if we were torn apart,
we'd go to get the other,
no matter how far.
Zero Two kept up her
end of the promise,
so I can't just sit
here and do nothing!
I absolutely cannot!
[ALL gasp]
I feel bad about
letting you all down,
but at the same time,
I want you to understand.
[GORO] What do you mean,
"you feel bad"?
What do you mean,
"you want us to understand"?
Have you ever spared a thought
for someone other than yourself?
What about the people
who are close to you?
Have you ever thought
about how they feel?
Never. That's how you are.
You run off, make your
own decisions,
and never stop to
think about us.
Papa and the adults
are gone now.
But forget freedom,
our hands are completely tied!
Have you stopped to think
about how worried we are
about all of this?
When someone collapses,
all we can do is watch.
Yet we're trying our
damned hardest to live on!
But here you are,
running off to die!
What are we supposed to
understand about you?
There are people doing
all they can to support you
because they want you to live!
And you trample their
feelings as you leave!
The hell do you want
understood about you?!
[HIRO]
Even so, I have to go.
[GORO gasps]
If Zero Two won't
smile for me again,
then honestly, I might
as well be dead.
[GORO exhales]
[ZOROME]
Hey, Goro! Knock it off!
[MIKU] Do you think we'll
ever find something like that?
Huh?
[MIKU] Something that
means the world to us.
That we'd choose over
anything else, like him?
[IKUNO]
It's different for each person.
[ICHIGO]
Goro...? Thank you.
[GORO]
For what?
[GORO] That was never
about how everyone felt.
It was all about me.
I'm the one scared of the
world that I chose myself.
[GORO]
That's me.
[ICHIGO]
Yeah.
Same here.
But... No one can swim in
the same river water twice.
So all we can do... is find
our own true path in life.
[ICHIGO] We'll keep looking
for it, until we find it.
Our lives have only
just begun, you know?
[BOY PARASITE A sobs]
[NANA grunts]
[HIRO gasps]
[GORO]
Hey.
[HIRO]
Where are you guys going?
We're taking you to find
Zero Two and bring her back.
[gasps]
[ZOROME] But we're not just
doing this for you, ya hear me?
If we don't go up there and
kick those guys' asses,
no amount of farming
can help us.
Letting them kill us or waiting
here to die isn't our style.
Exactly. Our lives have
only just begun, after all.
Couldn't have said
it better myself.
You'll have to take care of
things here while we're away.
Sure.
[9'a]
Let us join you.
[ICHIGO]
The Nines.
We don't want you to get
the wrong idea or anything.
The sole reason we were
created was to fight.
We're only interested in
fulfilling our purpose.
And outer space doesn't sound
too bad for a resting place.
We don't have any
intention of dying.
We'll be coming back home
to make even more fields
and continue living on,
come what may!
No matter how pathetic
it may make us all look.
[9'a chuckles]
[GORO]
Hiro.
You have made your decision.
I won't fight it anymore.
Now you and I are even.
This path, it's what we've
chosen in order to live.
You don't get to
fight it, either.
[GORO] Everything changes.
All things eventually pass.
And nothing remains stagnant.
Yes. Like a river.
But, if that nature of our world
scares you out appreciating
what you have now,
you'll never grasp any kind
of future for yourself
That's why... we reached out.