[PAPA, APE VICE CHIEF]
This is VIRM's will.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
Star Entity is a mass of life
that could disturb
the universe's peace.
[PAPA] As such, if the klaxosaur
princess were to take over
the implanting process,
we programmed it to explode.
[9'a]
Papa?
[APE VICE CHIEF]
The die has been cast.
[PAPA]
This planet...
[APE VICE CHIEF]
...will explode...
[PAPA, APE VICE CHIEF]
...leaving nothing behind.
[MALE SAGE A]
What's going on?
[MALE SAGE C]
Who are you?
[PAPA] We have assimilated
several lifeforms
from all over the universe,
and helped them break free of
the shells of their bodies.
[APE VICE CHIEF] And the time
has come for you humans
to embrace your evolution!
[MALE SAGE C gasps]
What?
[PAPA, APE VICE CHIEF]
There exists a form of pleasure
that is gentle and perpetual,
and you will now experience it!
Damn!
[HERO]
Zero Two...
[screaming]
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[001 screams]
[HIRO]
It's all or nothing.
[HIRO] What is this? Just how
long have you been alive?
You've been living
all by yourself
since before humans existed?
[gasps]
Darling.
[MALE FRANXX PILOT A] Command!
Please come in, command!
Papa!
[FUTOSHI] Uh, hey! Who exactly
are we supposed to fight here?
[ZOROME]
The klaxosaurs, obviously!
That's how it's always been!
[IKUNO] But she said the
ones that came from the sky
were invaders.
[KOKORO] It doesn't
matter who the enemy is.
All I can do is fight.
[FRANXX] Since the
detonation stalled once
Code Zero-One-Six connected...
[FRANXX]
It's a backdoor code.
Backdoor code?
[FRANXX] It's targeting
the Stampede mode.
They set it up so
the mode's overload
would cause an
internal explosion.
[FRANXX laughs]
They got me. They got me good!
If this thing blows,
the planet will go with it.
And Code Zero-One-Six
prevented that from happening?
[FRANXX]
All he's done is slow it down.
As things stand, it will
reach critical in...
[HACHI gasps]
[ZERO TWO] So, that's how much
time my darling bought us, huh?
[HACHI]
Code Zero-Zero-Two?
[MIKU] Don't you think it's
too dangerous to stay here?
What else are we
supposed to do?
[ICHIGO]
Hey, calm down.
We should assume we won't get
any more orders from above.
Which means we'll have to
deal with this ourselves.
[IKUNO] They were saying
some pretty strange stuff
in that last message.
Uh-huh. About using Star Entity
as a bomb or something.
They also said that the
whole planet would explode.
[grunts] Yeah, nothing
they said sounded normal.
[ZOROME]
What does that mean?
Wasn't that thing supposed
to put an end to the war?
[ICHIGO gasps]
[ICHIGO] We should go
and see for ourselves.
If the bomb thing is real, we
don't have time to stand around.
You're right. And I'm worried
about Hiro and Zero Two.
[MIKU]
Yeah, good point. Okay then.
[ICHIGO] We're heading back...
to the Gran Crevasse!
[HIRO screams]
[001] It's no use. VIRM got me.
It's over. We've lost.
These VIRM,
what exactly are they?
Who are these guys that
came from the sky?
The ones your people fought?
When I connected
with you, I felt it.
The passing of an
unbelievable amount of time.
When did it begin?
She said that I was a fake.
What was that all about?
What did she mean?
[FRANXX] She is the sole
survivor of the klaxo-sapiens,
and you... are her clone.
[001] It has been more than
60 million years now.
[001] We inhabited this planet,
as a civilization
far more advanced than yours.
[001]
But one day, VIRM arrived.
They were a group mind
with no physical bodies,
and they wanted us to join them.
[HIRO]
Join them?
[001] They were telling us
to cast aside our bodies.
We refused, and war broke out.
[001]
During that centuries-long war,
we reforged ourselves
into immortal weapons.
And evolved into what you
people call "klaxosaurs."
By the time we finally
fought off VIRM,
fighting and warfare
was all that remained
of our civilization.
We had even lost our
ability to procreate.
[001]
But things did not end there.
The enemy we had fought off
was but VIRM's vanguard.
With no innate form,
they kept expanding,
adding weapons of the planets
they devour to their arsenal.
[HIRO]
No.
[001] To prepare for
VIRM's inevitable return,
we went underground.
The weak turned themselves into
energy, and the strong combined,
evolving into even
stronger weapons.
[FRANXX] That is how the
klaxo-sapiens built Star Entity,
a collective mass
of klaxosaurs.
Only a klaxo-sapiens
can operate it.
The klaxosaur princess has
probably lived millions of years
for that very purpose.
[FRANXX] Zero Two, you were
created to operate Star Entity
on behalf of the human race.
I created you from her DNA.
[001]
Even if victory was impossible,
I wanted to take down as
many of them as I could,
but this is the end.
It's all over.
[HIRO grunts]
Is it really the end?
[001]
Huh?
Is there really nothing
more you can do?
[001]
That's right.
[FRANXX] Many specimens were
born, but failed to survive.
You were the only success.
Eventually, with the idea of
using them as either backups
or stamens, I created
clones using your cells, too.
But they didn't inherit
the klaxosaur blood.
[MIKU grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps] Clones from... my cells?
[FRANXX]
The Nines.
[ICHIGO]
It's you guys.
[9'a]
Why are you here?
You know as well as I do
this isn't your squad's post.
Leaving without permission can
be considered disobeying orders.
Return to your assignment.
When Papa gives you an order,
you follow it no matter what.
[IKUNO] That's meaningless at
this point! The bomb is going--
[9'e] That doesn't matter,
it's not your call to make.
It's Papa's.
[ICHIGO] And we can't
get in touch with him,
which means we're on our own!
We have to analyze and
make our own decisions!
Our own decisions?
Do you guys seriously think that
you're special or something?
Papa's words are absolute,
you understand?
[9'a]
Tsk. Damn monsters.
Kill every last one of them!
[9'a shouts]
Those guys are completely nuts!
[ICHIGO gasps]
[GORO]
Ichigo! Now's our chance!
[ICHIGO]
Oh, yeah! Hurry!
[KOKORO gasps]
[MITSURU grunting]
Kokoro! Let's go.
[KOKORO]
Uh, right.
What is with those guys anyway?
[9'e]
Delta! To your left!
[9'd grunts]
What?
[gasps]
[9'e screams]
[9'a]
Delta! Epsilon!
[9'd grunts]
[9'a]
Hang on, you two!
[9'y] We'll get rid
of them right away!
[9'd screams]
No! I don't wanna die!
[9'e screaming]
Help me!
[9'd whimpers, screams]
Screw every one of you.
Screw every one of you!
[9'a yells]
[ZERO TWO]
Okay, I'm going.
[HACHI]
Where?
[ZERO TWO]
To bring back my darling.
[HACHI]
Don't push yourself.
[ZERO TWO]
My darling is waiting for me.
[FRANXX]
What can you do there?
Star Entity is probably
rigged with VIRM traps.
Even if you took it back, you'd
only end up falling into them.
[ZERO TWO]
So what?
[FRANXX]
Hm?
[ZERO TWO]
The klaxosaur princess?
VIRM? I don't care.
I don't care if I'm a fake,
or a monster, or whatever.
My darling and I made a promise.
To be together forever.
And that we'd go get the
other if we were torn apart.
[HACHI] But we learned
the door to the entry point
only opens for
Code Zero-Zero-One.
[FRANXX]
Very well. I'll go with her.
[HACHI]
Doctor?
[gasps]
[MIKU screams]
[ICHIGO yells]
Everyone...
[ALL]
Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO]
Mm!
[FRANXX]
Zero-One-Six's connection has
delayed their plans,
if only briefly.
He is most definitely an
unknown factor to VIRM.
The klaxosaur princess,
Zero-One-Six, and you,
together, the three of you
could create a miracle.
You think so?
[FRANXX]
It's a highly optimistic view
with no basis whatsoever.
Some might call it blind hope.
Even so,
it's still a lot better than
standing no chance at all.
[MIKU]
Man, these guys don't give up!
[ZOROME]
Now there's another!
[ICHIGO gasps]
[GORO]
It's caved in!
[MITSURU]
No! We'll have to take a detour!
[ICHIGO] There's not
enough time for that!
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[IKUNO]
Get back, everyone.
[MIKU]
What are you doing, Ikuno?
[IKUNO] Futoshi! We're going
to open up a path!
Right!
[ICHIGO]
Wait, Ikuno! If you do that--
[ALL grunt]
[ICHIGO]
Are you okay?
--[IKUNO pants]
--[FUTOSHI] Ikuno! Your hair!
[ZOROME]
Damn it!
[IKUNO]
Ichigo! Move!
[ICHIGO]
How can I?
[KOKORO] I'll stay behind.
The rest of you, go on ahead.
[MIKU]
The hell we will!
[KOKORO]
Huh?
[MIKU]
We're staying with you!
You're not gonna
throw your life away!
[KOKORO]
But Miku...
[MITSURU]
Kokoro.
[KOKORO gasps]
I think our teammates are
making the right call on this.
We should fight together.
[KOKORO]
Mm.
[ZOROME]
Either way,
we'll need manpower to
hold these things off.
[MIKU] Okay, there you have it.
So get going already!
Ichigo.
[ICHIGO]
I understand.
[IKUNO]
Zero Two. Get Hiro for us.
[FUTOSHI]
After we save the world,
let's have a big feast together!
We'll even make a bunch
of your favorite sweets
things for it, too!
[ZERO TWO]
Mm.
[ICHIGO]
You take care of Chlorophytum!
And don't you guys dare die!
[GORO]
Let's go!
[ZOROME]
Welp, leader's orders.
Miku? We're gonna survive,
no matter what!
[MIKU]
Of course we are!
[KOKORO gasps]
[MITSURU]
Here they come!
[HIRO breathes heavily]
[001]
Why? Why do you still struggle?
This battle was never
yours to fight.
I used to be the same.
[001]
Huh?
I was the same way
as you people.
I never doubted for a second
that my purpose in life
was to fight, and I
wasn't afraid to die.
But you know what
I came to learn?
You don't call that living.
Meeting Zero Two
helped me understand.
Crying, Laughing,
Falling in love.
The time we spend doing those
things is truly valuable.
And I realized I wanted
to protect it all.
[001 gasps]
[HIRO] But if we march into
death, we'll lose everything.
It'll all be gone.
And I'm not having that!
I will never give up,
you hear me!
I promised her... that I'd
be with her forever.
[001 gasps]
I don't just live
to fight anymore.
I'm going to fight to live.
What the...? Is that Hringhorni?
Who's operating it?
[9'a]
Hey, Papa. Say something.
What are we to do?
[GORO]
Crap! It's catchin' up!
[ICHIGO]
Zero Two! How much farther?
[ZERO TWO]
I see it!
[ICHIGO grunts]
[gasps] It's over there!
[GORO] They keep coming.
Go! Get Hiro for us!
[ICHIGO] Both of you had
better come back together.
If either of you is missing,
there's going to be hell to pay!
Thanks, you two.
[GORO]
You're not getting past!
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ICHIGO screams]
Damn it!
[ZERO TWO]
Ichigo! Goro!
[FRANXX]
Dig in. It's your master's arm.
[FRANXX groans]
[ZERO TWO]
Doctor! Why?
[FRANXX] That contains
the princess's cells.
They didn't turn me into a
klaxosaur like I wanted,
but this will do,
[FRANXX]
Get going.
Doctor.
[FRANXX] It's the least
I could do to atone.
I won't ask for forgiveness.
Feel free to hate me.
I deserve it for what
I've done to you.
[growling]
[ZERO TWO]
Are you telling me to ride you?
All right, then.
[ZERO TWO]
Hey.
[FRANXX]
Hm?
[ZERO TWO] Did you take
me to Plantation 13,
to reunite me with my darling?
[FRANXX]
Who knows?
It's not like I was
expecting you two
to rekindle what you had.
It was just a scientist's whim.
A fancy.
[ZERO TWO]
That's so you.
I should say this before I go.
[FRANXX]
Hm?
'Cause you created me and
helped me meet my darling.
So, thank you.
[FRANXX]
When did she become so... human?
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Thank you.
[ZERO TWO]
Strelizia.
Wait for me... darling.
Darling!
[ZERO TWO] Darling! I'm here!
I kept my promise!
Hey! Darling!
Wake up! Open your eyes!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Please, talk to me!
Hey, hey... Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I'm talking to you!
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Oh, no...
[alarm buzzes]
So then, it didn't work.
[ZERO TWO]
I will... never accept this.
And I will never give up!
Please wait for me, darling.
[001]
Is this what living is for you?
I'm beginning to understand.
We believed by
abandoning our ties
and embracing solitude,
we could perfect ourselves
and become stronger.
However... perhaps some lives
only shine in unison
with another.
[001]
Very well.
I shall give you every ounce of
strength that remains within me.
Whether you can take over the
controls will be up to you.
[001]
This planet and its future...
...I stake... on the two of you.
[ZERO TWO]
Darling. Darling?
[HIRO]
Zero Two.
I did it. I kept my promise.
I believed you would.
Everybody helped me
get back to you.
[HIRO]
Zero Two, I missed you.
[ZERO TWO]
Same here, darling.
[BOTH chuckle]
What is this?
[001] Humans, we shall
take flight once more.
Decide whether you want to
fight or accept your ruin.
[APE VICE CHIEF] Strelizia is
rejecting all attempts
at interference.
[PAPA]
It broke free of our program?
[ZERO TWO] Right now, I feel you
closer to me than ever before.
I know what you're thinking,
like the back of my own hand.
No matter what happens,
from here on out,
our hearts will always
be as one, darling!
[HIRO shouts]
[FRANXX]
I see it! I see it!
Ah. How beautiful you are,
my Apus, Strelizia.
Apus!
[APE VICE CHIEF]
We have no choice.
We'll settle for the lance of
life built from klaxosaurs.
We wanted more, but we'll
withdraw for now.
[PAPA]
But know that we will return.
And when do, we'll bring
our full army,
and erase this planet
from existence.
[9'a]
Papa...
[pants]
It looks like we
did it, Zero Two.
Zero Two?