[IKUNO] Everything comes
to an end eventually.
The only difference is whether
it happens sooner or later.
[IKUNO] And even as we
sense that the end is nigh,
we spend another day idling
in the cradle of our lives.
♪
Doesn't that hurt you?
[ZERO TWO]
Not a bit.
[ZERO TWO giggles]
Miku. I'm ready now.
Ta-da!
Well?
[MIKU] It looks perfect!
I'm sure Hiro will love it, too!
[ZERO TWO giggles]
Hey! We got trouble!
Hey.
[ICHIGO]
The Nines. Why are you here?
[9'a] We're here to check
on you. On Papa's orders.
[GORO] Papa? Are you saying...
we weren't cast aside?
[9'a laughs]
Of course not!
In fact, Papa has been worried
sick about every one of you.
He's... He's really
been worried?
What the heck? You guys coulda
come and told us sooner!
[ALL sigh, chuckle]
Anyway, this is horrible.
[9'y] It's no environment
for children to live in.
[9'a] Hm. Now then, we'll be
needing our own rooms.
Would you mind
getting those ready?
You want to stay here?
Don't you remember?
I said I took a liking
to you guys, right?
[ICHIGO sighs] All the squads
that managed to survive
have been gathered
in one place?
[9'b]
Yeah, in a camp of sorts.
And all of the FRANXX are being
fine-tuned there as well.
Oh. I see. What happened
with us, then?
Why were we the only
ones who were left out?
It's not what Papa wanted,
that's for sure.
Nana and Hachi should
know more about it.
I wonder why they didn't
tell you anything.
[9'g]
Hey, why are you crying?
It's because I'm so relieved.
It seems silly now that
you're here, but I was honestly
really afraid that we'd
been left here to die.
Gotta say, you guys
are surprisingly nice!
So, please, eat up!
Consider it a thanks for
bringing us good news!
Come on, don't be shy!
This stuff tastes pretty good...
When I saw you
standing by the door,
I assumed you were here
to take Zero Two back.
[9'e laughs] You shouldn't
think of us as her babysitters,
just her squadmates.
That said, however.
She didn't exactly seem
pleased to see us herself.
How long are you going to
continue playing human?
You know you'll never
be the same as them.
They're certainly
a unique squad,
although hopelessly imperfect.
They are fundamentally different
from you and us, Iota.
[ZERO TWO]
Zero Two.
[9'a gasps]
What was that?
That's my name. It's Zero Two.
You're throwing away the Special
Forces codename Papa gave you?
That right. My darling
gave me this name,
so it's important to me.
[9'a laughs]
Well then I wish you luck, Iota.
[HIRO]
Zero Two. What is that?
Oh, you mean this? Miku made it.
[HIRO]
Wow.
Quit staring at me.
[HIRO chuckles]
It looks great.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Never mind. You can
stare just this once.
[HIRO chuckles]
It looks like they've
grown a bit bigger.
You think they're really horns?
It must be from riding with me.
Or maybe, it's because
you ingested my blood
when we were little.
Either way, I've drastically
altered your destiny, huh?
Darling.
[HIRO]
This actually makes me happy.
It's like I'm the
same as you now.
[ZERO TWO]
Right.
[ZERO TWO] Y'know, darling.
That picture book?
It's inside me.
I ate it when they were
trying to erase my memories.
I didn't want to forget.
[ZERO TWO] I started
wanting to become human,
because I wanted to
see you again.
That's when they told
me it was possible.
That I could be human
if I killed klaxosaurs.
I shouldn't have believed them.
Papa and the others
told you that?
Hey. Show me yours.
[HIRO]
Huh?
You know. You drew
a page too, right?
[HIRO gasps]
Uh! No, this is, uh...
[ZERO TWO]
Let me see, already.
No way!
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
Lemme see!
[ZERO TWO laughs]
What the heck?
That's exactly why I
didn't wanna show you.
Too bad. This page is approved.
Wait. Seriously?
This picture is perfect.
I love it.
[KOKORO gasps]
Are you all right?
Uh, yes, I am. Thank you.
What are you doing over here?
Just exploring the place.
Don't tell the others, okay?
[KOKORO giggles]
You can count on me.
Have a good night, then.
[9'a] Reproduction.
Childbirth. Fetuses.
These are all concepts
Papa hasn't taught anyone.
With the Nines here, it's just
a matter of waiting.
Surely someone will come
to get us eventually, right?
Will that mean the end
of this life we have?
That is the natural assumption.
[MITSURU] But... the thought
of leaving this place,
makes me a little bit sad.
[KOKORO]
Huh?
I mean, we only began spending
time together like this
after I came here.
Mitsuru.
Uh, Kokoro?
Your body. It's much tougher
than a girl's. So strange.
[MITSURU gasps]
Boys' and girls' bodies are
so different from each other.
But then, there actually
is a reason for this.
What are you talking about?
[KOKORO]
Well...
...I read that a boy and a
girl can create a new life.
And the way they do it is by
joining their bodies together.
Uh. Hold on.
[KOKORO gulps]
I wondered, "What's it mean?"
And... I believe it
represents hope.
[MITSURU gasps]
[MITSURU grunts]
Kokoro! What are you doing?
I was just...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Were you two really just
gonna try to stick
your bodies together?
What is that?!
D'ja learn it from
Hiro and Zero two?
Uh, did you need something?
[ZOROME]
Huh? Oh.
I'm supposed to remind you
that you're on water duty.
Anyway, what is it that
you guys are up to?!
[MITSURU] I'll go get the
water right now, okay?
Ugh, what the heck, man?
Then hurry up and do it already.
[KOKORO sighs]
[MITSURU]
Why'd you do that?
It's so out of nowhere.
No, it isn't. I've been thinking
about it for a long time.
[MITSURU gasps]
[footsteps]
[HIRO]
Oh.
Hiro.
[MITSURU] I don't understand
what Kokoro's thinking.
It makes no sense.
I see. You know,
you've changed a little bit.
Until just recently,
you'd always been distancing
yourself from the rest of us.
[MITSURU gasps]
Of course, it's my fault
you were doing that.
I'm the reason, aren't I?
Because I broke our promise.
[HIRO] But now you've taken
an interest in someone else.
You want to know Kokoro better.
You want to understand
what she's thinking.
Wait, you think, I want
to know her better?
Uh-huh. That's what it
means to love someone.
I mean, I love Zero Two
and wanna know her better.
[MITSURU] Oh. So that's what
this is. I love Kokoro.
Sorry if I'm mistaken.
Your situation
could be different.
I only know how it is for me.
It's okay. I think that's
very much like you.
I'm glad that we talked.
We haven't done this
in a long time.
Oh! There he is!
[BOTH]
Hm?
We heard about you...
and her. Blame Zorome.
I have to say, I'm not
the least bit surprised.
Hey all I did was casually
ask if a boy and girl
getting touchy-feely was
some sorta cool thing to do!
That's enough!
Stop being such a baby!
Mitsuru! Tell me,
did you... kiss her?!
[MITSURU]
Uh, well...
Not my Kokoro! Someone wake
me from this nightmare!
[IKUNO]
Settle down.
[FUTOSHI] But, if you two
are happy, who am I to...
[FUTOSHI sobs]
Oh. Hey, everybody. Do any
of you recognize this?
[gasps]
It looks like you do.
Then surely you won't mind
giving us an explanation.
Right, Code Five-Five-Six?
[9'a] You are the one who
dropped this book, aren't you?
But this is strange.
It wouldn't be provided
in the study here,
and it certainly
doesn't belong to you.
What's the meaning of this?
[MIKU]
Uh, what is that?
[ZOROME]
What's that book about?
Well, um...
[KOKORO] I'm sorry for
not telling you all.
Everyone? I want to make a baby.
[MIKU]
A baby?
[ICHIGO]
Like animal babies?
[FUTOSHI] And how exactly
would you make one?
Wow. Okay. You are aware
Papa has banned that, right?
[ZOROME gasps] Wait, really?
Sounds like trouble.
She tell you about this?
[MITSURU]
Mm-mm.
[KOKORO]
O-Okay, sure.
But still, is it really
that terrible a thing?
I mean, this practice is how the
adults, as well as ourselves,
and every other human,
comes to be born.
Hold on.
Are you saying that Papa
isn't the one who created us?
[KOKORO]
I am.
The truth is, we're the
same as any other animal.
It's what we've done
since ancient times.
That's how. The way every
living thing has been keeping
their species going for
thousands of years!
So... the reason we
have boys and girls
must be because of that.
And... this may
be selfish of me,
but I want to leave
a mark on the world.
Leave something
behind before I'm gone.
[9'a]
Leave a mark?
Yes. We've lived
our entire lives
believing we had no purpose
other than riding the FRANXX
into battle against
the klaxosaurs.
But you know what? That might
not actually be true!
We could carry new lives
and leave them here
as part of the future.
When I learned
that was possible,
it made me feel so happy!
--That's why--
--[9'a] Absolutely disgusting.
[KOKORO]
Huh?
I mean you. You're disgusting.
[KOKORO gasps]
[9'a]
This is ridiculous.
Humans have evolved and cast
their reproductive functions
aside in the process.
If you reject that,
then we will all have to
go back to conforming
to one gender or another.
But, what about...?
Has this thought crossed
your mind? I'm sure it has.
Gender is a pain.
An annoyance only tolerated
for the sake of
operating the FRANXX.
And that's all it is.
That's not...!
[9'y whistles]
Ikuno?
[IKUNO] A pain, huh?
Even if it is, then so what?
[sighs] Humans also cast
away their tendency
to be ruled by emotions.
Especially ones like that.
Such things serve absolutely
no purpose in life.
And yet, look at you people.
Why, you!
Cut it out, Ikuno!
You need to calm down!
--[IKUNO] Let me go!
--[NANA] That's enough!
[GORO]
Nana! Hachi!
[NANA] This is why I didn't
want to let the Nines in!
I knew it would be
nothing but trouble!
[NANA grunts]
Perhaps, but they were sent
here on Papa's command.
We couldn't just turn them away.
Since it's come to this,
we ought to put an
end to the test.
What test? What do you mean?
We were acting on
the doctor's explicit orders
not to contact you in any
form this past month.
He informed us this would
be Squad 13's final test.
Of course we still monitored
you the entire time.
Which means, we saw you
interact with Mitsuru.
We know what you
were attempting.
[KOKORO gasps]
So you want to
make a baby, huh?
You know that's something
nobody's allowed to even
speak of, let alone do.
[KOKORO]
But... why not?
Why do our bodies still have
reproductive organs, then?
Solely because they're necessary
for piloting the FRANXX.
[KOKORO gasps]
That's why only children
possess them,
and that's all there is to it.
Don't go thinking you and your
squad are somehow special.
Then what about these feelings?
Why do we still have emotions
if they don't serve a purpose?
[NANA grunts]
Quiet!
Nana, what...?
[NANA]
I said shut up!
Return to your dorm.
We'll give you your
orders in due time.
[NANA grunts]
[HACHI]
How long?
[NANA]
For a week or so now.
Watching them go about their
lives made me feel so irritated.
[HACHI sighs]
[9'a] Well, well. Did someone
relapse into puberty?
Me? Never. I can't be
going through puberty!
Haven't you two
undergone the procedure?
Emotional Indoctrination.
You should have when
you were both parasites.
Relapsing is really bad news.
You should have her replaced
with a new Nana, Hachi.
[NANA]
Huh?
I hope you go back to
doing your actual job
from now on, instead of getting
into mischief with the doctor.
Well. I'll be reporting
this to Papa and the rest.
[HACHI grunts]
[FRANXX]
So. Nana is useless now.
Doctor. I believe continuing
will be difficult.
[FRANXX] Oh, I'm sure. But I
gained some intriguing data.
The development of humanity's
original reproductive instincts.
That's far beyond
my expectations.
[MALE SAGE B]
This development differs greatly
from human civilization
and culture.
I never expected
the klaxosaurs
to still possess
such technology.
[MALE SAGE B] It's a great
pleasure to meet you,
Princess of the Klaxosaurs.
Humans and klaxosaurs
have waged a war
spanning close to a century,
and you have shown truly
admirable spirit and fortitude.
But it is now time for
this protracted war
to be consigned
to the history books.
You no longer stand
any chance of victory.
Cease your resistance at
once and surrender to us.
--[001 hums]
--[ALL groan]
[MALE SAGE B] Are these words?
Sent directly to the brain?
What? What are you saying?
That can't be!
[MALE SAGE D]
Prepare to die, Princess!
[MALE SAGE B]
Stop. No. Don't!
[MALE SAGE D shouts]
[MALE SAGE B]
Wait!
[roaring]
[MALE SAGE B]
No! This isn't what we wanted!
We only came here to
ask you to surrender!
[SOLDIERS gasp, scream]
[001]
Damned human wannabes.
[FUTOSHI] Kokoro sure is
taking a while to return.
[ICHIGO]
Yeah.
[MIKU groans] I had no
idea she was thinking about
stuff like that. I wish she
had talked to me about it.
It's not her fault. Everyone has
things they can't talk about.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[MIKU] Do you guys think we
can make babies? Like, really?
How're we supposed to know?
It's not like we were
taught about it.
Another question is,
if Papa didn't create us,
how exactly were we born?
Again, how are we
supposed to know?
[GORO]
What do you think, Hiro?
I'm not sure. I mean,
it might be possible.
We may have the potential
to do something
Papa never told us about.
Like what Kokoro said.
To leave something
for the future.
The future.
To leave a mark.
I'm so envious.
[HIRO]
Hm?
[MIKU]
Envious? Of what?
Of leaving something behind.
My body's incapable
of doing that.
Zero Two.
It's wonderful.
You're all wonderful.
You have the ability to
decide your futures,
with your own hearts.
[KOKORO crying]
[MITSURU]
Kokoro.
[KOKORO]
I was wrong. About everything.
[MITSURU exhales]
[KOKORO] I'm sorry I tried to
force you to go along with it.
I'm so sorry.
[MITSURU]
Don't apologize.
You weren't forcing
me to do anything.
Liar!
[KOKORO]
Don't bother trying to be nice.
Just leave me alone.
I will not!
[MITSURU] Don't decide things
on your own! I'm here!
I want you to lean on me more!
So please, Kokoro, I want
to make you happy!
I don't understand. Is it so
wrong to wanna make new life?
Why can't we? Aren't we allowed
to think about the future?
[IKUNO] Everything comes
to an end eventually.
The only difference is whether
it happens sooner or later.
[IKUNO] As for what comes
after that, we have no idea.
We know nothing.
[IKUNO]
Nothing.
[PAPA]
The klaxosaur princess
chose to go down the
path of annihilation.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
How foolish.
So now they'll feel the pain of
having their earth scorched.
And by their own
creation no less.
[9'a]
We're back, Papa.
And there's something
you need to know about.
♪