[KOKORO "This will surely
be our last battle."
That's what everyone believed.
But while the rest had
those thoughts running
through their heads,
a different emotion had
begun lurking inside me.
And I didn't know
what to do with it.
Hiro, I'm gonna stay here.
Mitsuru.
I understand.
You've chosen this battlefield.
Why did you stay behind?
I may not be able to pilot now,
but you could have found
another partner
and gone with them.
I stayed because I wanted to.
It's my responsibility, as well.
Responsibility?
Even when you don't
remember a thing?
[KOKORO]
I told you:
I don't expect
anything from you.
So please, don't mind me.
♪
[ZOROME screams]
[MIKU]
You okay, Zorome?
These Gs are nuts!
My guts are crumpling up!
And just think, this is
after the G-Cancellor
is already abating
a lot of it, too.
Seriously?
[IKUNO] Don't know why,
but this feels right.
I can move a lot more freely.
[MIKU] Yeah! Fighting in space
should be no problem at all!
And check out these weapons!
We finally have
identical loadouts!
It's like we've become
a real team at last!
You dope.
In case you haven't noticed,
we've always been a real team.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Oh, have we?
[GORO] We're here.
We're really in space, huh?
[ICHIGO]
Mm. So far from home.
[NANA] New space equipment
for the Franxx,
and a ship full of provisions.
What if Hiro's
belief is correct
and the klaxosaurs actually did
leave all of this behind for us?
That would mean...
...humanity has been allowed to
join the fight to defend Earth.
Even if that is the case,
do we really have
the right to do so?
[HACHI] If we want to
ensure humanity's survival,
all we can do is believe.
Wow, we actually
managed to connect.
Sure did! Like I said,
we Nines have the ability
to be both stamens and pistils.
Besides, you put too much
strain on your partner.
No ordinary pistil
could handle it.
[NANA] You're not exactly
in the best shape either.
Don't push yourself.
Gee, thanks for the warning.
Well, give me a taste of what
you can do, Zero-One-Six!
[HIRO gasps]
[9'a] You want to go
see Iota, don't you?
Wait a second. This feels...
[9'a]
Of course it does.
After all, we're Iota's clones.
It's funny how it worked out.
To think my final
partner is a human.
[HACHI]
All FRANXX: Return to ship!
We'll begin accelerating
to cruising speed shortly.
[ICHIGO]
Roger.
[KOKORO]
What do your eyes see?
Everybody else is out
there fighting in space.
But not me.
I've lost my ability
to fight with them.
I'm... not a parasite anymore.
[NANA]
You understand this?
Somewhat, yes.
How are the controls so similar?
Perhaps the reality
of the situation is...
...klaxo-sapiens weren't
that different from humans.
That said, most of the
navigation system is automated.
We're only tagging along
for the ride, basically.
What does this route lead to?
What are we going to
find in Mars orbit?
[HACHI]
Who knows?
But Strelitzia Apus is
heading there as we speak.
Looks like getting
there won't be easy.
For some reason,
I don't want those children
to hurt themselves any more
than they have already had to.
Isn't that weird?
I mean, I watched over them as
tools of warfare for so long.
That feeling. Is having
it really so wrong?
The children's sole purpose
in life was to fight.
If this truly is
their final battle,
then in their lives afterwards,
don't you think they'll
need someone like you?
[HIRO gasps]
--Yo.
--Hey.
[HIRO]
Goro. Ichigo.
We've always been
attached at the hip.
Now we're in space together.
Let's get Zero Two.
No matter what it takes.
[ICHIGO] C'mon, Goro.
Don't you have something to say?
Uh, I guess...
I'm sorry for hitting you.
Heh! What the heck?
Forget it!
Y'know, if you were
just gonna apologize,
you shouldn't have hit
him in the first place.
[GORO]
Oh, shut it.
--[ICHIGO, HIRO laugh]
--[alarm sounds]
[HACHI] Detecting what
seems to be a VIRM Fleet!
All FRANXX, prepare for combat!
[NANA]
We're not slowing down!
Is it going to plow straight
through to where Apus is?
[HACHI] The VIRM are
trying to surround Apus!
But the klaxosaurs are forming
a defensive line around it, too.
[GORO]
We're charging right in there?
[ZOROME] Damn it!
Aren't we gonna fight back?
All the energy output
is focused on the shield!
The ship's going to ignore
the enemy and head for Apus!
[FUTOSHI]
Over there!
[IKUNO]
We see it!
[MIKU]
Strelitzia Apus!
[ICHIGO gasps]
Hiro!
[HACHI] All units.
Follow Alpha's lead!
[GROUP]
Roger!
[ICHIGO]
Here we go, you guys!
[NANA] There's a huge number
of VIRM units by Apus!
Be careful!
[ZOROME] Why isn't Apus
firing that giant laser?
[9'a]
If it could, it would have.
[9'a] Maybe it really
isn't fully operational
without a stamen.
[GORO]
Incoming!
[ICHIGO] Everyone,
scatter and take them out!
[grunts]
[GORO]
Hiro!
You just ignore the enemy
and head directly for Apus!
Zorome!
All right, let's do this!
Follow me!
[MIKU] Leave the enemies
in front to us!
[ZOROME]
Eat that!
[ICHIGO]
Chlorophytum!
[IKUNO]
We've got your backs!
[ICHIGO yells]
[MIKU gasps]
[ZOROME]
What the...?
Don't forget about
the two of us!
All of you can
sit back and relax.
[ZOROME]
Ha!
Like I'd let you hospital
runaways do all the work!
[ICHIGO gasps]
Look!
[FUTOSHI] They're trying
to keep us away from Apus.
[GORO] Have they
realized Hiro's with us?
[IKUNO] It'll be bad news
if they block us off.
[ICHIGO] Hiro, use your Franxx's
speed to cut through.
We'll cover you.
[HIRO]
Got it.
Zorome! Miku!
Don't try to push it!
If we don't push
ourselves now...
[MIKU]
...then when will we?
Haaa!
[MIKU, ZOROME]
Get going! Hiro!
[HIRO]
We caught up!
[9'a] Look there.
It's the entrance.
Nice!
What?
[HIRO]
Why, you!
[HIRO grunts]
[HIRO]
If that's not gonna work...
[HIRO grunts]
[9'a]
Well, this is not good.
It looks like this is
as far as I go with you.
[HIRO]
What?
[HIRO grunts, gasps]
[9'a]
Meeting you guys
helped me learn a little
about being human.
But my home is the battlefield,
and nowhere else.
Tell Iota "hi" for me.
[HIRO]
Alpha!
[9'a]
It's been kinda fun, I guess.
[HIRO] Zero Two, why did you
leave me and run off alone?
[HIRO]
Together, we are one.
"We'll always be together."
Didn't we promise
each other that?
[HIRO]
Answer me. Zero Two!
[thunder rumbles]
[KOKORO]
No! You can't!
What's the matter?
[KOKORO]
Zero Two!
What is... happening to you?
No, don't!
[thunder rumbles]
[gasps]
Zero Two. This thing, is it you?
[HIRO]
If it is...
If it's you,
then please, consume me.
[HIRO] Is this the picture
book in Zero Two's mind?
[ZERO TWO]
Stay away.
Why'd you come?
[HIRO]
To see you.
Why did you leave?
[ZERO TWO] Because, darling,
I want you to remain human.
[HIRO]
I want to be with you!
[ZERO TWO]
I can't be with you.
[HIRO]
Why?
[ZERO TWO]
I just can't.
[HIRO breathes raggedly]
[FUTOSHI]
The ship!
[ZOROME gasps]
[ZOROME]
Hey, look!
[GORO]
Oh, crap!
[ICHIGO] C'mon, guys,
we're gonna provide back up!
[IKUNO] Not letting us go
without a fight, huh?
[9'y]
We'll distract them for you!
[9'b]
Go!
[ZOROME]
Thanks!
So then, should we
go in a blaze of glory?
[9'b]
Not a bad idea.
[NANA]
Let's move to another ship!
[HACHI, NANA grunt]
[NANA gasps]
[HACHI]
So, this is it, huh?
Leave me and go.
You don't get to say that
after keeping me alive.
To hell with that!
You listen to me.
It's your duty to watch
over their futures, too!
[footsteps]
[HACHI]
What's that?
[NANA] The ship was
equipped with a bomb?
--[PAPA] Cease your resistance.
--[NANA gasps]
We know that voice.
[APE VICE CHIEF] Is there any
point at all to this warfare?
[PAPA] Eventually, all
lifeforms will merge with us.
[APE VICE CHIEF] Surrender
yourself to the gentle,
perpetual pleasure we offer.
[PAPA]
Our utopia is free of all hatred
and discrimination
between species.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
Klaxosaurs? Humanity?
Such distinctions
won't matter anymore.
Equality for all!
[PAPA]
But beyond that,
we will attain an endless
and peaceful slumber.
And at the same time, endless
and relentless evolution.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
Rejecting that to march toward
your destruction
is far too foolish.
[PAPA]
Now, become one with us.
[HACHI]
To the adults,
that very well may have
sounded like utopia.
But that is not where
the children belong.
In perpetual tranquility,
the flames of their lives
will never burn as bright.
[HACHI] It isn't a matter
of right or wrong.
This is simply the path
that the children,
and humanity, have chosen.
[MIKU]
Things are getting pretty rough!
How much longer does Hiro need?
Don't worry.
He's always pulled
through in the past.
[ICHIGO] And we're not
the only ones struggling.
Yeah. Those two must be fighting
back on Earth just as hard!
[IKUNO]
That's right!
[MITSURU] Kokoro!
It's not safe! Get inside!
Just leave us be!
Zero Two wants to
stay right here!
Yeah, but... it's bad
for your body!
I don't care.
I will protect her!
[gasps]
Now that I'm not a parasite
anymore, I have nothing left.
Nothing I can do!
So I want to at least
be by her side!
Please, just let me stay.
All right, then I will as well.
I'll stay with you both!
Go away!
I've told you so many times
you don't need to feel respons--
[MITSURU]
It's not about responsibility!
Please don't say that
you have nothing.
If you don't, then neither do I!
[gasps]
[MITSURU]
But that's not true.
I've found my reason to live.
In you.
I want to protect you
and that baby's future.
I'm a weakling
and I don't really
understand what love is.
I don't.
But still, if I'm with you,
then I can keep walking.
That's what I've
come to believe.
[KOKORO gasps]
What the...
You still have that?
But why?
Why do you say my name
even though it hurts you?
Even without our memories,
we can start over again.
I'll call your name as
many times as you want.
This right here?
This is our battle to fight.
[KOKORO sobs]
Mitsuru. Mitsuru.
Mitsuru!
[MITSURU]
Kokoro. Kokoro.
--Kokoro!
--Mitsuru!
[ZERO TWO] I was always
a monster, so whatever.
But you?
I want you to live as a human.
That's why...
I can't be with you.
[HIRO] We promised
we'd always be together.
[ZERO TWO]
Stay away.
I'm fine... by myself.
[HIRO]
Liar.
If you really are, then why
is your last page left blank?
Don't fly off alone.
Please, Zero Two,
let me stay here with you.
Together, let's rewrite
that story's ending.
Darling.
Uh, Zero Two?
[KOKORO gasps]
What's going on?
[HIRO] I hereby vow
to never let you go.
[ZERO TWO]
Okay.
[GROUP]
Zero Two!
[ICHIGO]
He got to see her!
[GORO]
Wait, what?
Isn't that...?
[MIKU]
What the heck is that?
[ZERO TWO]
A warp gate.
[MIKU, ICHIGO gasp]
[IKUNO]
"Warp gate"?
Yeah.
The klaxo-sapiens built it.
[HIRO]
Hey, guys? Listen.
Zero Two and I are going
to go through that gate
and leave the solar system.
[IKUNO]
"Leave the solar system"?
Wait, what? Right now?
[ICHIGO gasps]
No way.
Whoa, whoa, wait a second!
You met up with Zero Two
like you wanted.
Why not head back to Earth?
[HIRO] Apus and the gate's
system are linked.
That means... neither of us
can stop the process.
Besides, the gate
will close soon.
[MIKU]
You're kidding.
[ZOROME]
This can't be happening.
[ICHIGO]
I don't get why.
Why do you two have to
go through that thing?
So we can finally put
an end to this war.
Now, I see. This is
what that bomb is for.
--[ICHIGO] Then let's all go!
--[HIRO] You can't.
[HIRO] Only Apus can withstand
going through the gate.
[FUTOSHI] But what are you
gonna do all by yourselves?
[IKUNO] And won't the
enemy's main force
be much larger
than this one was?
Yeah.
We'll need to take
them by surprise.
[GORO]
You will come back, right?
[MIKU]
Oh, no.
[ICHIGO]
I won't let you!
If that's your answer,
you can't go!
Leader's orders!
Come back alive, both of you!
Ichigo.
Exactly! I won't stand for it.
Come back to us, Hiro!
Yeah, I'm not gonna
accept goodbye like this!
[MIKU]
Me neither!
Squad 13 isn't complete
without the two of you around!
[FUTOSHI]
So, come back with Zero Two!
[IKUNO]
Yeah!
You guys.
[ICHIGO]
Zero Two!
It doesn't matter
how long it takes.
Make sure you come
back with Hiro!
We'll build a home
and wait for you!
[chuckles] You are
always so bossy!
I promise.
I'll come back to you
with my darling.
[KOKORO] Everyone has their
own feelings and desires.
We're all looking for
somewhere to belong.
Strelitzia looked so
beautiful at that moment.
Or so everyone who saw
it would tell us later.
[KOKORO] Right now,
all we can do is pray.
Pray that what is
waiting for those two...
...is a happy ending.