[HIRO] The act of bringing
two pairs of lips together,
which we'd never heard of,
was called a "kiss" she said.
[HACHI]
Commence connecting.
[HIRO] The day after
the klaxosaur attack,
the start-up ritual
picked up where it left off,
only in a much quieter fashion.
This time, Papa and the
other adults weren't around
to witness it.
They told me the huge FRANXX
I rode was named Strelizia.
But as far as to what
occurred after I got in it,
I have no recollection.
Despite that, though, I still
believe that it all happened.
That I was able to
fly by my own power.
I'm no longer a nestling.
And so I swore to myself
to never run away again.
♪
[ICHIGO]
Meow-meow!
You're just a little kitty,
aren't you? Yes, you are.
[HIRO]
Ichigo?
[ICHIGO gasps]
Uh, Hiro!
[HIRO] Please say that
you weren't out here
waiting for me.
Yeah, I was.
You shouldn't run off first
thing in the morning.
I understand it may
be awkward for you,
but this is your home now,
so you should try to settle in.
[ICHIGO] Did you hear
Naomi was all right?
They took her to the hospital.
[HIRO]
Yeah. I heard.
Were you the one?
Piloting that FRANXX, I mean.
I can't quite remember,
so I wanna ride in it again.
Then, I can be sure.
[ICHIGO]
"Again"?
You do know that girl
isn't part of our squad.
I don't care.
As long as I can pilot.
[ICHIGO] I've heard rumors
about her. They're awful.
Like how she's never had a
partner who's been able to ride
with her more than three times.
Do you know why that is?
Because they don't
make it out alive!
[ICHIGO] I don't know
if that's true or not,
but I think it would be best
if you stayed away from her.
But, if I don't pilot,
I'm as good as dead anyway.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[ICHIGO]
Hiro...
[GORO]
You guys need to get in here.
That weird girl's
in our mess hall!
[HIRO gasp]
[plate clatters]
[MIKU groans]
[MIKU]
What is she still doing here?
[KOKORO]
What a strange person.
She must like sweet things.
[MIKU] In case you forgot,
no "person" has horns!
[ICHIGO]
That's enough.
Don't forget she's
our savior, so be nice.
[MIKU]
Hmph.
What I wanna know is if she
really has klaxosaur blood.
And, why does she have a single
digit code but no one else?
She's nothing like the
rumors said she'd be.
[GORO chuckles] And her eating
habits kinda kill her charm.
I can't believe all her
injuries healed so quickly.
[ZOROME]
Hey, there!
I wanted to say, watching you
fight was a treat.
And if you'd like,
you can always have
Zorome the Great ride with you.
Someone of your skill
deserves much better
than having that wuss
in her FRANXX.
So what do you say
that I come over and--
Ah! What are you doing?!
You ruined my Sunday best!
Ah! Hey, don't you
walk away from me!
[HIRO gasps]
Hi. We should be
eating together.
It makes things sweeter.
I've got a question.
Did I actually manage
to pilot that FRANXX?
[ZERO TWO giggles] You sure did.
And you were great, darling.
[ALL]
D-Darling?
Uh. What's that mean?
[KOKORO]
I've never heard of it before.
Hey, wait! You gotta
fix my shirt!
[KOKORO]
I wonder what it means.
[HIRO] Then it's true.
The other day...
...I really did pilot a FRANXX!
Okay! Attention!
[KOKORO]
Nana!
[NANA]
Ahem. All right.
Effective immediately, I'm
taking over as your caretaker
like I was in the Garden.
It's official.
APE HQ assigned me to
the 13th Plantation Corps.
Thanks for your cooperation!
[GORO]
Yes! Talk about luck!
[ICHIGO]
Nana?
[NANA]
Yes, Ichigo?
[ICHIGO]
Is Zero Two staying here?
[NANA]
We're still awaiting orders
on what we're doing with her.
But we do know that she won't
be working with you guys.
[HIRO gasps]
[NANA] Come. You know
where your seat is.
[ZERO TWO] Aw. But this one's
so much more comfortable.
[HIRO]
Wait, hold on. Hey! Zero Two!
If you don't mind, please let me
ride in your FRANXX again.
There's something I
need to be sure of.
[NANA] That's not for
either of you to decide.
Papa and the others will give
you your new orders in due time.
So until then, just sit tight.
Papa? Give him orders?
[HIRO exhales]
I don't get that girl.
[NANA] You can't be running
off whenever you please.
[ZERO TWO] I just wanted
to eat with my darling.
[NANA] Avoid contact
with the parasites.
They're nowhere near ready
to handle someone like you.
[ZERO TWO] I feel like I'm
gonna suffocate in here.
[FEMALE PA VOICE]
Confirmed appearance of one
Mohorovicic-class klaxosaur
at Plantation 13.
Intercepted and
neutralized by Strelizia.
Fuel stockpile down to
54 percent. Currently anchored.
Requesting kissing
with Plantation 26.
[PAPA]
Authorized.
[FEMALE PA VOICE]
Roger.
Kissing will commence
in 175 hours.
[MALE SAGE A] We've received
word that Strelizia
has stayed back
at Plantation 13.
[MALE SAGE B] Another one of
that girl's whims, no doubt.
Dr. Franxx spoils
her too much.
[APE VICE CHIEF] I'm most
interested in these numbers.
It appears we're looking
at a very rare sample
from a very unique specimen.
There're no apparent signs
of physical aging.
[MALE SAGE D]
It's Code Zero-One-Six.
That's him, isn't it?
[MALE SAGE C]
Unacceptable.
Without good cause,
mixing with the special
specimen will taint her blood.
She must be recalled at once!
[PAPA] We all saw how she
shone in that battle.
It's worth investigating.
Let's wait and see.
[GORO] I still can't believe
you were able to fight
that klaxosaur.
What was it like?
[HIRO] Honestly, I don't
remember much about it.
Only... the way that it felt.
I see. Well, either way,
I'm glad you decided
to stay with us.
Maybe you just perform
better under pressure.
Ya sure got me beat
[ZOROME]
Out of my way!
I don't believe for a single
millisecond that you
managed to pilot a FRANXX
before the rest of us.
A wuss like you? C'mon! Hmph.
[HIRO]
Hm.
[MIKU] Ugh! Why do they make
these so tiny? And tight!
[KOKORO]
Connecting feels so strange.
I hope we get used to it soon.
It's nothing like how
the training units felt.
[KOKORO yelps]
[MIKU] But no amount of
training could prepare
the young parasites for
this sensation, for it is like
their bodies are being
stirred up from the inside!
Here it comes! Are you ready?
[IKUNO] Cut it out. I don't
wanna think about it.
[ICHIGO]
Was it rough for you guys?
I thought it felt weird,
but I dunno.
[ICHIGO] Personally, the whole
thing put me more at ease.
Like I'd become
one with another.
[MIKU]
What?
[KOKORO]
Sounds amazing.
I wish my numbers
were as high as yours.
I guess you and Goro must
be really compatible.
[MIKU] "The elite double digits
are made for each other."
I'm so happy for you.
Oh, gee, thanks.
[MIKU] But speaking
of elite, how about Hiro?
Out of nowhere, he shows up with
a girl and after one ride, boop!
She calls him "darling." He, he!
I don't really get it,
but they may end up a good--
--[thump]
--[yelps]
[KOKORO gasps]
[MIKU]
Huh. What's her problem?
[HACHI] I'll give you your
strategic objectives.
But all decisions on the field
will be made by the
lead FRANXX, Delphinium.
[ICHIGO]
Roger.
What'd Ichigo ever do
to become leader?
Now. We'll begin the drill.
This'll be your first
one in a real FRANXX,
so relax and stay calm. So long
as you trust your partner
and follow their movements,
you'll do fine.
Commence connecting.
[KOKORO, MIKU gasp]
Don't make weird noises!
[MIKU]
It's a natural reaction!
Partners can't afford
to be out of synch.
Their para-capacity
will fluctuate.
You must trust your partner and
accept them wholeheartedly.
You okay?
[ICHIGO]
I'm fine. Keep going.
How was that?
It didn't suck, right?
[KOKORO]
Mm-mm. You did just fine!
[FUTOSHI giggles]
We're a good match, aren't we?
[ZOROME] Enough, you two,
spare us the touchy-feely crap!
If anyone should
be bragging, it's me.
I was the first to finish!
Ya hear that, "double-digits"!
And don't you forget it!
So wound up.
We shouldn't compete
with each other.
[ZOROME]
Ha! Spoken like a loser!
[MIKU] Zorome, slow down!
You're being too rough!
[ZOROME gasps]
Whoa. Whoa!
[ICHIGO]
That was close.
[MIKU]
Thank you.
[ICHIGO]
The stamen controls handling,
but the pistil connects
to the FRANXX.
So, you have to make sure she
can keep up with your movements.
Thanks. Know-it-all.
[HACHI] Line up in formation.
Delphinium in the center.
Then, advance!
[ALL]
Roger!
[HIRO]
It happened. I know it did.
If they would just let
me ride with Zero Two
in Strelizia again, then I...
[NANA] A startup trial
in an actual FRANXX?
I've almost figured out
the secret to connecting.
I'm so close.
Hey! Wait a sec!
Why'd you pick Hiro?
"Hiro"? You mean my darling?
What does that even mean?
Look, everyone's grateful that
you stopped the klaxosaur
the other day.
But, from now on, I want
you to stay away from Hiro!
Why's that?
Because you're not
part of our squad.
That means you'll leave one day.
So you shouldn't be
getting Hiro's hopes up.
[ZERO TWO] Oh? And what
are you to my darling?
I'm the leader of this squad.
[ZERO TWO]
Hm.
Uh, hey.
[ICHIGO gasps]
You taste sweet. I like that.
[ICHIGO grunts]
[FUTOSHI] Do you think we'll be
able to fight like that one day?
[FUTOSHI grunts]
Against the klaxosaurs.
Like what Hiro did in
that girl's FRANXX.
Huh?
What he did out there is not
what I would call "piloting."
You know that jerk
can't handle a FRANXX.
[FUTOSHI] But it did move
around with him inside.
And Papa seems to have taken
an interest in Hiro, too.
[ZOROME]
So what?
[MITSURU] I heard another rumor
about that Zero Two pistil.
They say she has the special
ability to pilot a FRANXX
all by herself. You saw
that four-legged form?
She controlled that alone.
Hiro was no pilot,
he was along for the ride
as cargo and nothing more.
What did I tell you?!
There's no way that loser
piloted a FRANXX before us!
Huh?
[ZOROME] Don't go thinkin'
you're hot stuff, you hear me?
Bullseye! I'm number one!
Sorry, pal.
I really thought you were
gonna be able to dodge that.
Where've you been?
Playing with yourself
in a training unit?
That is the best you can do.
The closest thing you
can get to action
is hitching a ride with a girl!
[laughs]
Huh? What's with you?
You wanna fight me?
Zero Two said I
piloted that thing.
You wouldn't forget your
first time if you did!
Once I get another chance,
I'll prove it to you!
[ZOROME growls]
You know where to find me!
[ICHIGO gasps]
Hey! What are you doing?
[GORO]
Break it up!
[FUTOSHI gasps]
Knock it off.
Let me go, he's
had this coming!
Damn you, Hiro! You're nothing
but a waste of space!
[ZOROME grunts]
I can do it.
I just need a chance.
[ZOROME grunts]
--Yeah.
--[phone rings]
[ICHIGO]
It's Nana.
A mock battle,
with me in a FRANXX?
That is correct.
And depending on
how well you do,
we may promote you to parasite.
[HIRO gasps]
Way to go!
[HACHI]
Pick your partner.
[ZERO TWO]
I'll do it.
[HIRO]
You will?
Of course. You are
my darling, after all.
[ICHIGO]
Wait just a moment.
Please, allow me
to be his partner.
[GORO]
Ichigo.
[ICHIGO] With all due respect,
she's not part of our squad.
Besides, if the purpose
is to test Hiro's aptitude,
it should work just
as well with me.
But then why does it have
to be you of all people?
Don't forget. You already
have a partner,
and yet you want to ride
with someone else?
[NANA] That's enough. I don't
like where this is going.
Zero Two.
HQ hasn't authorized the use
of Strelizia at this time.
The only way for Hiro
to do the mock battle
is to partner with someone
from his squad.
[ZERO TWO]
Boo. That sucks... Oh, well.
My injuries haven't
healed yet, anyway.
[HIRO]
Wait, what?
So. I'll let you have
him just this once.
Better make the most of it.
Take care of my darling.
Then it's settled. We agreed?
[ICHIGO]
Yes.
[HIRO gasps]
Wait!
[MITSURU]
Hmph.
[HACHI] Does anyone want to
volunteer as their opponents?
[ZOROME]
We will!
[MIKU grunts] Excuse me?!
Shouldn't we talk about this?
Back me up. This is our chance
to prove what we can do, okay?
[MIKU grunts]
We'll do it.
[NANA]
All right.
The battle will be tomorrow.
[ZOROME]
Wait, wait, wait!
Why can't we duke
it our right now?
[GORO] I guess Zorome can't let
go of the fight you had earlier.
Yeah. Sorry I have to use
your partner for this.
[phone rings]
Is everything ready?
Yup. Gotta go.
'Kay. Later.
And, Hiro, it's fine.
I couldn't have told Ichigo
not to do it if I wanted.
Thanks. I'm gonna make
this one count, I swear.
Good. I know you can do it.
[door clatters]
Hey!
You and I got some unfinished
business to handle, pal!
[MIKU] Given your
partner's track record,
I may just beat you
this time, "Great Leader."
[ICHIGO] Fine by me. This test
isn't about winning or losing.
[FUTOSHI] Miku's as pumped
for this as Zorome.
[ICHIGO] I don't care if
we lose. All that matters
is that we prove that Hiro
really can pilot a FRANXX.
[ICHIGO] Just relax and
focus on connecting.
I'll take care of the rest.
[HIRO]
Got it.
[HACHI]
Begin the mock battle.
[ZOROME]
Ready when you are.
[ICHIGO]
Focus.
[HIRO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
This'll work.
I can draw out Hiro's
ability too. I know it!
[HIRO] This feeling... It's like
I'm entering Ichigo's mind.
[ICHIGO] That's right.
Keep going. I've got you!
[ZOROME]
No way. This can't be!
[HIRO]
We did it!
Way to go, Hiro!
--Wow!
--Good.
[NANA]
But now the real test begins.
It feels... just like before!
[ICHIGO]
Now fight!
[HIRO]
Yeah!
[ZOROME]
All right, bring it on!
Huh?
[ZOROME gasps]
[ZOROME]
What the...?
[MIKU]
They stopped.
[ICHIGO]
No. Why now? What wrong?
Not like this!
Time out! Give us
three minutes, okay?
--Wait, what?
--[MIKU] Huh?
[MIKU gasps]
There're no time outs!
[HIRO] Why isn't it working?
We have to keep moving.
Come on! Damn it!
Why'd this happen?
I piloted just fine before!
[ICHIGO pants]
What's wrong?
I dunno. It stopped.
Is it my fault?
I don't think so.
Is there something
Zero Two did that I'm not?
[HIRO]
I don't know. I don't remember!
[ICHIGO]
It's okay, there's no rush.
Just relax and
maybe it'll come back.
The kiss.
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
She "kissed" me first.
'Kay. What's a "kiss"?
[HIRO] It's, uh. We put
our lips together.
There was some flash
of light. And boom.
Hold on.
That's what you were doing
during the klaxosaur attack?
[HIRO] It's not like we
were fooling around.
She just did it as
soon as I got in.
Truth be told, I didn't know
what was happening.
But she made it sound
like a special thing.
[ICHIGO]
Fine. Let's try it.
[HIRO gasps]
[ICHIGO] But close your eyes
so I'm not embarrassed.
Wait, hold on a second.
[ICHIGO] We can't move
unless we do this, right?
If that's all it takes,
I don't mind.
It's not a big deal.
[HIRO gasps]
Yeah, but...
Stop talking.
You're trembling.
Ichigo.
[MIKU] Hey! Hasn't it been more
than three minutes by now?
It sure has. They've had
their chance, let's do this.
[ZOROME] Okay, losers.
We're takin' you out.
[ICHIGO]
Well?
[HIRO] I don't feel a thing.
This time, it didn't work.
[BOTH gasp]
[ZOROME]
Aw, man, this is too easy.
Let's try... once more!
[ZOROME] Thanks for helping me
prove that I really am the best.
Y'know, if you want, I don't
have a problem taking over
as Delphinium's pilot, too!
[MIKU gasps]
Are you trying to get
in with another girl?
You're such a creep, Zorome!
[FUTOSHI gasps]
[KOKORO]
Huh?
[HACHI] The trust between
the two partners
has a direct influence on how
well their FRANXX handles.
Should it be thrown
out of whack...
[ZOROME grunts]
What's going on?
[MIKU, ZOROME grunt]
Ichigo, give us a status
report! You hear me?
[MIKU] Can you hurry
and get it up already?
[ZOROME] What do you
think I'm trying to do?
[NANA]
Ichigo, don't!
Piloting a FRANXX
alone is dangerous!
[ZOROME yelps]
[ICHIGO]
Damn it!
[MIKU, ZOROME grunt]
[ALL gasp]
[IKUNO, KOKORO cough]
[FUTOSHI yelps]
Of all the reckless stunts...
[HACHI]
Ahem. Both FRANXX are down,
so that concludes
the mock battle.
[ICHIGO panting]
[HIRO] The gentle touch
of her trembling lips,
overwhelmed me with guilt.
That feeling of
having flown before,
quickly slipped
through my fingers,
leaving me shackled to
the ground once again.
[HIRO]
All I felt in its place...
...was the binding tie of a
thousand invisible threads.
[HIRO]
I'm sorry.
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
Don't apologize.
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
You were awful.
♪