[IKUNO grunts]
[MIKU grunts]
[KOKORO grunts]
[ICHIGO] Almost done.
Let's gang up and end this!
[ICHIGO gasps]
[MIKU coughs]
What is this stuff?
[KOKORO gasps]
It's super sticky!
[IKUNO grunts]
Yeah, but...
[ZERO TWO]
It doesn't hurt.
[KOKORO]
Huh. I guess it's harmless.
[MIKU]
So that was just for show?
How dare you spew this
disgusting gunk on our FRANXX!
[ICHIGO]
Let's hit it again, guys.
Stay with the plan.
[HIRO gasps]
Now what's going on?
[FUTOSHI gasps]
Kokoro!
[HIRO grunts, gasps]
[gasps]
[KOKORO, MIKUE grunt]
[MIKU]
Zorome? Why aren't we attacking?
Can you hear me in there?
I-I do! Don't worry,
everything's fine.
[KOKORO]
Futoshi?
Yeah. We're good,
no need for concern.
[ZOROME, FUTOSHI grunt]
[ICHIGO] Focus. We're in
the middle of a battle.
Right. Let's do it!
[gasps]
[ZERO TWO]
Darling! Let's finish it off!
[gasps]
Oh! Sure!
[ZERO TWO shouts]
[gasps]
[ZERO TWO]
Darling?
We have a problem, Zero Two.
You're being exposed!
[FUTOSHI, ZOROME]
Don't tell her, dumbass!
[GIRLS]
Uh?
[MIKU screams]
My parasite suit!
[GIRLS scream]
♪
[GIRLS grunt]
[GORO]
You've got it wrong!
The only reason we didn't tell
you about your parasite suits
melting is 'cause we didn't
want to distract you
in the middle of battle!
In my case...
...I simply found you too
beautiful for words, Kokoro!
Believe me, this comes
straight from the heart!
[KOKORO gasps]
--[FUTOSHI gasps]
--This is stupid.
[FUTOSHI sighs]
What's the big deal?
It's not like us seein'
ya hurt you at all.
[MIKU] Excuse me?!
What did you say?
Whoa, hold on!
Zero Two once told me that
parasites are better off
being, uh, well, they're better
off being a little pervy!
Isn't that right, Zero Two?
[ZERO TWO]
Mm-hmm.
What the hell?
[BOYS grunt]
[MIKU] I can't believe they were
ogling us in middle of a battle!
Wait. You don't think they were
doing it at the beach, too?
[ICHIGO]
That's how boys are.
Unbelievable! Those creeps!
And here I thought we'd finally
started linking up smoothly.
This can have a negative
impact on team morale.
[KOKORO] Uh, hey.
Maybe we should calm down.
No, I'm done!
After this, I don't wanna be
around the boys anymore!
Know what we should do?
Put an end to it.
[OTHERS]
Huh?
No more communal
life with the boys!
[MIKU]
Listen up.
No boys are allowed on
this side of the line.
Who died and put you in charge?
Just try and stop me!
Zorome.
If you cross that line, you're
gonna regret it, big time.
[BOYS gasp]
[FRANXX]
Ah, puberty.
Yes, but for so many members
of one squad to begin it
at the same time,
it's unheard of.
[NANA] Statistics indicate
that it's always been,
at most, just one or two
members starting it together.
[HACHI] But this time,
it's practically everyone.
Highly unusual.
[FRANXX] But that's what
makes it so intriguing!
If we're going by
the APE manual,
we're supposed to intervene
and resolve any and all issues
before they get out of hand.
[FRANXX]
Listen to yourself!
What would be the point of this
test team if we did that?
Just observe what happens
and give me detailed
reports afterwards.
Don't you dare interfere.
And don't you let the geezers
find out about this either.
[MIKU] Did you see the
looks on the boys' faces?
Serves them right!
[ICHIGO, MIKU gasp]
What's the matter?
[ALL grunt]
We gotta rein her in.
--[door clatters]
--[GIRLS gasp]
[ZOROME chuckles]
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?
Since you've blocked
us from the baths,
we went and took a dip in
the lake. And it felt amazing.
[MIKU] Okay, would it
kill you to get dressed?
Did you hear me?
Sorry, but if we're on
our side of the line,
we don't have to
listen to you.
[MIKU, ICHIGO grunt]
[ZOROME imitates chicken]
[MIKU] What in the heck
was that all about?
[IKUNO]
They're trying to provoke us.
[ICHIGO]
I bet it was Goro's idea.
There's no way Zorome or
Futoshi could've thought of it.
How come they get to spend their
morning goofing off at the lake
while we get stuck cleaning
the baths? It's not fair!
We can't really
complain about that.
That's true, we declared the
baths off limits to the boys
when we split the house in half.
[MIKU]
But it's not fair! Aw, man.
Of all the things we
could have to do ourselves,
why'd it have to be cleaning?
I mean, are the invisible
caretakers so busy
cooking our food and
doing our laundry
that they couldn't
handle this, too?
[clock chiming]
[ALL gasp]
Sorry, girls, but we've
taken over this area.
We noticed you hadn't
taped it off, so...
[ZOROME]
Mmm! Oh, it's so good!
Today's breakfast is exquisite!
You! You're heartless!
Y'know, you're right.
So how about we agree to
forget all of these silly rules,
and eat together again, eh?
It's a trap.
Agreed. Miku, no! Stop!
[ZERO TWO]
Hm?
[MIKU whimpers]
No!
[GORO sighs]
How pigheaded.
[HIRO]
Everyone's being so stubborn.
It's starting to get really bad.
We need to work this thing out.
Is that how you feel, Darling?
[HIRO]
Uh?
'Cause I'm the opposite.
In fact, I think things
could be spiced up.
[HIRO]
Huh?
[KOKORO sighs]
You're here again! Do you
have an interest in flowers?
Not really.
[KOKORO]
Then why are you here?
It's a good hideaway spot
when I want to be alone.
That's why I'm here.
Ah... You probably don't know,
but I begged Nana to let me
take care of this greenhouse.
We had some seeds, so I've
been planting and growing them
while studying up on things.
Have you heard of the
language of flowers?
This is a hibiscus.
In floral terms that means
"delicate beauty."
And over there's the cattleya
orchid which means "alluring."
[KOKORO] Um. I'm not bothering
you by chatting like this, am I?
You mean because of
the fight? It's stupid.
I can't be bothered
with that stuff.
[KOKORO]
Really? That's so cool.
Why's it cool?
When you're expected
to toe the line,
it takes a lot of
courage to refuse.
I know because I
was too afraid to.
[KOKORO gasps]
[MITSURU gasps]
[MITSURU]
You brought it back with you?
Uh, yeah.
I see. Well, it doesn't
matter to me either way.
[door clatters]
[MIKU]
Oh, I'm starving!
[IKUNO]
And whose fault is that?
[MIKU] Look, you made
your point, alright?
That's why I'm trying so hard
to find us things to eat.
[MIKU] So, this is what
the first floor's like.
I've never been
down here before.
Why's it sealed off?
Because nobody's using it?
[ICHIGO] How long do you
think this fight will go on?
Honestly... I'd like
it to last forever.
[IKUNO gasps]
Tastes like someone
has a secret.
[IKUNO yelps]
What?!
[MIKU]
Wait!
Whose side are you on?
[ICHIGO] We'd prefer you
cooperate with us, of course.
I hate to break it to you,
but this whole fight is lame.
You're just fooling around.
[MIKU gasps]
This isn't a game!
Maybe to you it's lame,
but we're serious.
Uh, about that.
You are? Wow. Hmm...
All right, then. I'll join
up with your camp.
[OTHERS]
Hmph.
--[ZOROME gasps]
--What's up?
[ZERO TWO] They said you
can use the bath now.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
[HIRO] Zero Two said we can
use the bath? Are you sure?
Oh, yeah!
Sounds to me like the girls
are waving the white flag.
[ALL gasping]
Wait! It's not what
it looks like--
[GIRLS scream]
Girls! Listen! It's
Zero Two's fault!
Oh, crap. There's no way
we can stop them now!
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
Hey, wait!
[HIRO pants]
Zero Two! How could
you do that to us?
'Cause we're fighting, darling.
Now come at me with
all you've got.
[ZERO TWO laughs]
[HIRO grunts]
I'm telling you,
this was all a setup!
Shut up!
--[ZERO TWO giggles]
--[HIRO grunts]
--[HIRO] Hold it!
[ZERO TWO]
C'mon, Darling,
you have to be faster
if you want to catch me!
[HIRO grunts]
Oh, you are on!
Get out, perverts! I'm gonna
break you creeps in half!
We should leave
while we still can!
[FUTOSHI]
Hey! Our clothes are gone!
[ZOROME]
What?!
[ZERO TWO giggles]
[HIRO gasps, grunts]
[HIRO pants]
There's nowhere left to run.
It's over for you--
[gasps]
[ZERO TWO laughs]
Darling, you pervert!
[gasps]
[HIRO grunts, laughs]
All right. Why'd you do this?
[ZERO TWO] Because. I wanted
to try taking part in a
real human fight for once.
Zero Two...
Whaddaya think, darling?
Tell me. Do I seem
more human to you now?
[HIRO gasps]
Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[HIRO gasps]
[shouts]
That's it! We're sick
and tired of this crap!
We're the ones
sick of your crap!
[ZOROME]
Shut up!
Why are you girls always
looking down on us boys?
[MIKU] Why don't you boys ever
spare a thought for us girls?
[ZOROME]
Boo-hoo. Being a girl's so hard!
All of you knock
it off right now!
[ALL]
Uh...
[NANA] What would you do
if a klaxosaur attacked
in the middle of
this silly feud?
Can you sortie like this?
Because I certainly
don't think so.
All of you are parasites now!
Don't forget what comes first
and foremost in your lives!
[ALL]
'Kay.
These children. They're nothing
like the others.
Zero Two joining in on
their little skirmish
was highly unexpected.
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
That was so much fun!
I absolutely loved how naughty
and rebellious that was!
What were you thinking?
Explain yourself!
[ZERO TWO] If you keep
half-assing things like that,
you'll end up like
the adults one day.
[GIRLS gasp]
I'm telling you. If you have
something you wanna say,
you better spit it
out while you can.
[GIRLS gasp]
Just because, sooner or later,
you're all going to die.
[GIRLS gasp]
[doors clatter]
Man, I'm pissed! Where do
the girls get off being
so condescending to
us all the time?
They're like that because they
don't think highly of us.
Thanks. But no one asked
you for your calm analysis!
Ugh! Screw this crap,
I'm done with it.
I'm through with
the girls for good.
I feel bad, but if
I'm being honest,
I actually thought
that was kinda fun.
[ZOROME]
Huh?!
Zero Two did, too.
She was laughing.
Really hard. Y'know,
now that I think about it,
we should try to consider
our parter's feelings more.
Why should we bother to do that?
They're nothing but
weirdo wackjobs!
[HIRO]
True. I don't get them either.
But that's exactly why I started
wanting to know more about her.
That way, I might be able
to give her better support
when she needs it.
If you're talking
about Zero Two,
then you're barking
up the wrong tree.
She's extraordinary,
the ultimate pistil
that's never needed help
from anybody, even you.
[HIRO]
No, Zero Two's a normal girl.
And it's not just her.
Their job as pistils
means they rely on us
to handle the controls.
But then, when we
go into battle,
it's their frail bodies
taking the brunt of it.
Oh, wow. Yeah, that must
be rough on them.
[HIRO] Despite that, they keep
connecting to the FRANXX
and doing their best.
They place their trust in us.
Watching Zero Two like that,
it made me think.
I want to become stronger.
To take care of her.
Better than I can now.
You're right. The girls give
it their all in every battle.
It's wrong of us to
be back there ogling
while they struggle.
Of course they'd want
nothing to do with us.
I can be a man
about this, too, okay?
I'll admit it, even I
feel the need to look
after my partner and
take care of her.
And, believe me, I don't like
seeing the girls in pain
any more than you guys.
Well, then there's only
one thing for us to do.
[ICHIGO]
"Sooner or later we'll all die."
[KOKORO grunts]
Um. Okay! Y'know what?
I don't think we should
let this go on any longer!
There are some things
we can't do by ourselves.
But we can do them if we
work together with the boys!
And it's not just a few things
either, there are lots of them!
The most obvious being
piloting the FRANXX.
And yes, I know.
The boys are perverts.
I can't even imagine what's
going on in their heads
most of the time.
It's clear that boys and
girls are nothing alike,
but that's why it's good
for us to be together!
After all, that's how--
Well, that's how it gets
to be born, I think.
Like, the future.
And hope. And stuff.
So that's why we should, uh...
Wow, Kokoro. It's not like
you to be so assertive.
Yeah. Surprised me.
[ICHIGO] But still,
as unexpected as that was,
you make a good point.
[KOKORO]
Huh?
Yeah, we can't just be the
ones who complain all the time.
It's not right.
Whoa! Hold on a second!
You're not thinking
of forgiving the boys!
II know it's hard, but we
can't go on like this.
[MIKU grunts] Oh, really?
Fine, suit yourselves!
I'm not letting this one go,
even if I'm on my own!
[KOKORO gasps]
Miku, wait!
I'm just saying, I'm not
gonna beg for forgiveness.
You're still hung up on that?
[BOYS gasp]
Goro... We can't find
Miku anywhere.
Please, you have to
help us find her!
[BOYS gasp]
[FUTOSHI]
Miku! Where are you!
[ALL]
Miku!
[ZOROME]
You can come out now!
[ALL]
Miku!
[MIKU]
Listen to them.
Everyone's friends again
like nothing happened!
Well, too bad. I'm not
leaving this room.
[MIKU]
This looks like...
[MIKU gasps]
[MIKU]
It can't be...
[ZOROME grunts]
[KOKORO]
Miku! Oh, thank goodness!
We were worried sick!
What's wrong?
What is this place?
A room belonging to some former
Squad 13 parasites, I'd say.
Former.
Squad 13?
Of course. The plantation had
a defensive squad in the past.
Makes sense.
And then, in time, we were
assigned to defend here as well.
[ZOROME] So, how come
they aren't here now?
Well? How come?
They died, obviously.
[gasps]
They couldn't make it
back here alive.
[MIKU whimpers]
[GORO sighs]
[GORO]
We won't survive, either,
unless we get to know
each other better.
It's time. We need to make up.
'Kay, so...
I apologize. I'm sorry.
Also, you have my word, I'll
try to not leer at you anymore.
[MIKU]
You'll try and fail.
[ZOROME gasps]
[MIKU] I'm way too cute
for you not to leer at me.
[ZOROME gasps]
You can a bit. Just don't
take it too far, okay?
[ZOROME gasps]
Yeah, okay.
[OTHERS sigh]
[MIKU]
Inside that old room,
sat a vase by the window,
with lilacs in it.
I couldn't help but wonder.
What were the former Squad 13
parasites thinking
when they placed them there?
There's no way for us to know
that now. But the next day,
we went back there and replaced
them with brand new lilacs.
[MIKU]
In the language of flowers,
the lilac means friendship,
fond memories, and also, youth.
[MIKU]
Hey, knock it off, Zorome!
[ZOROME]
What'd I do?
[MIKU] You were eyeing
me again, admit it!
[ZOROME]
I wasn't even looking at you!
[MIKU]
Oh, please.
Zero Two. Always speak
your mind with me.
Don't hold anything back.
Oh? Why should I?
Because. I want to
get to know you better.
[ZERO TWO] Darling. Grab on
to me and never let go.
♪