Oh, twenty-two!
Eighty-eight!
Double-zero!
[GODA]
A hundred?
[KONG] Train your eyes
to track the ball's spin,
and you will read the numbers.
They're like nothin' else.
[COMMERCIAL NARRATOR 7A]
Step out into the world.
The world's first shoes
made especially for mats!
[KIMURA]
He's so cool!
I mean...
So not cool.
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 2C]
Eight eighty-eight!
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 2B]
No, six-ninety-six!
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 2A]
Um...
[KIMURA]
Three-twenty-four!
Yeah, son,
that's how it's done!
Yeah right, idiot.
You saw it before it started.
[panting]
That was friggin' pathetic!
Again!
[HOSHINO]
Can I ask one thing?
[TAMURA]
You may not.
Jeez, just tell me!
When do I play again?
[TAMURA] This'll be your life
'til you break one minute.
I've had enough of this.
I wanna work on my game now!
Quit your whining!
If you don't do what I say,
I'm gonna smack you good!
Now, go on!
And make it snappy!
[panting]
Come on, kid,
pretend I'm one of your
cute little chippies!
Get your butt up here
and gimme some o' that sugar!
[retching noise]
[TAMURA]
And no pukin'!
Show some respect
for this place!
Aw, gimme a break. Damn!
You think I'm puking my
guts out for the fun of it?
You mean, spiteful old hag!
There ya go, Peco,
that's the spirit!
Love ya, kid!
Could we please not go there?
Kills my motivation.
[TAMURA]
Oh, now, hush!
It's gonna be
dark before long.
So pick up the pace.
Ready, set, go!
[HOSHINO]
Screw... this... crap!
Come on,
just a little more.
Almost there, darling!
One more step!
Dig deep!
[groaning]
Way to show some guts.
I'm proud of ya.
Okay, now let's go again.
I hate you!
All right, pal,
let's see ya hit my Ultra
Super Knuckle Sinker Ball!
--Toriya!
--[TAKAMURA] Piece of cake!
[OTA] Throw home!
Throw home! Hurry up!
Uh, wait, I can explain.
Hey, the hell
is your problem, jerk?
Give us our ball back, huh?
[OTA] All right, time to do
some cool-down exercises, guys.
What?
Hey, Ota...
Y'know, Tsukimoto,
there are fish that actually
choose to live in the backwater.
They're content with it.
It's something in their nature
that sadly can
just never change!
Taku Kazama, head table
tennis coach at Kaio Academy.
Good to meet you.
[panting]
[HOSHINO]
There!
Ha! Did ya see that?
I just crushed it!
Back to the dojo, then.
[HOSHINO laughing]
Aw, come here and
gimme some love, Old Lady!
We're like the best couple ever!
Y'know, kid,
you might be right.
We'd spare no expense to
give you everything you need.
Come play for Kaio, Tsukimoto.
Your talent will
just wither and die
if you stay in this place.
You must know it's a total dump.
Hey.
[coughs]
[TSUKIMOTO] Does Coach
Koizumi know about this?
Of course, he's been consulted.
He agrees that it's
a great opportunity.
And in terms of your future,
he said it's the
best thing for you.
My future.
Really?
I must say,
I was rather surprised
to learn Koizumi
was coaching here.
Last place I
expected to find him.
Why, who is he?
[TAKU]
Butterfly Jo.
My hero.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Listen, I...
Yes, Mr. Tsukimoto,
what is it?
Well, I...
It's just that...
I apologize
for that, sir.
Don't worry about it.
Whatever that boy is chasing,
it's not money
or fame or success.
Those aren't the
only reasons to play.
Koizumi, your grandfather.
Your father.
Table tennis players
take many forms.
Perhaps, but Dad did it wrong.
And he had no talent.
Put that aside.
Tell me, are you playing
the kind of table tennis
you believe in?
You know that
I worry about you.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
He just wasn't popular.
There aren't
enough wreaths here.
Ryuichi, go order five more!
And Emiko, of all
times to be sick!
If your husband wasn't
doing such crap business,
you wouldn't get all
these strange diseases!
[EMIKO]
Mother is fine.
All families have
their own sets of rules,
so please, just try
to bear with it.
[TAKU] So kiddo,
who would your hero be?
There are no heroes.
[KOIZUMI] Sorry if it
seemed like I was trying
to get rid of you,
Mr. Tsukimoto.
But this old man
can't give you
the coaching a player
with your skills deserves.
We both know we've
reached the limit
of what I can teach you.
Guess I figured
if you went to Kaio,
you'd finally have
some room to grow.
Yeah, but, sir--
Huh?
[TSUKIMOTO] I got Sakuma
kicked out, remember?
How do you think Kaio
will react if I show up there?
[KOIZUMI] It's not like you to
let something like that bother--
Well even I have feelings.
I get sad or happy
like anyone else does.
Here I go.
Hey! Wait for me, yeah?
You'll wear yourself
out at that pace!
Didn't you hear
what I said, boy?
Slow down! Slow down!
Holy cow, Chump!
This dojo you
teach at is massive!
It's like bigger
than a shopping mall!
Peco.
This is not some measly dojo!
Athletes can't just
wander in here!
Their potential must be
recognized by the state!
Which means you've
been recognized, kid.
Congrats.
Hold on, Mom, not so fast!
There are rules!
Ooh, a Ping-Pong girl!
And hey!
Quit calling me "Chump!"
Yeah, yeah,
hurry and take us in.
[MICHIO]
Everyone!
Hoshino here will be
practicing with us from now on!
So welcome him with open arms!
Understood?
[NATIONAL TRAINING
PLAYERS] Yes, sir!
Yutaka Hoshino. Call me Peco.
Sixteen, Capricorn,
Type-O, fast offense.
It's a pleasure
to meet all of you!
[KOKUBU]
Three more minutes!
[NATIONAL TRAINING
PLAYERS] Yes, sir!
You call that
a fast offense, Peco?
C'mon, move, move, move!
Trying!
[MICHIO] Gotta keep
your eye on the ball!
Don't just trust your gut!
Use your eyes, kid!
Time!
Kokubu, let's switch.
Sure!
This is hard!
[HAMA-CHON] Has our little robot
finally gone totally haywire?
[TAKAMURA] Good luck trying
to find tech support
for a freak like that.
So your boy Smile
ran away, did he?
[KOIZUMI]
Yeah.
I've tried calling his house,
but no one's picked up.
His folks split up when
he was still real young.
Dad's out of the
picture completely,
and Mom won't be
home until morning.
[KOIZUMI]
And here I thought
I was doing right
by the boy, but...
That's why people
run away from you.
[KOIZUMI]
Huh?
You're always
doing that, you know.
Acting all timid and reserved,
worried about how
your students feel.
They don't respond to that crap.
Kids need clarity.
If you truly
care about the boy,
grab him in your arms,
squeeze him tight
and give him a big ol' kiss.
But if you can't give
him the love he needs,
then get the hell
out of his life.
This is so dumb.
[PECO'S BROTHER A]
Come on, Peco, wake up!
[PECO'S BROTHER B]
Chump's gonna be so mad!
[PECO'S BROTHER C]
Ooh, you're not supposed
to call him "Chump."
[PECO'S BROTHER A] Come on,
we gotta wake him up!
[PECO'S BROTHER B]
Peco!
[PECO'S BROTHER C]
[PECO'S BROTHER A]
What do we do?
[HOSHINO] You know, I gotta
give at least some of the credit
for this victory
to my loyal fans
and all their support!
I mean it! You guys
are the greatest!
What's my dream?
Well, obviously, I wouldn't mind
winning a couple gold
medals at the Olympics!
And I'd love a part in
an Akagi Nyugyo commercial!
[humming]
[KOIZUMI]
Welcome back, son.
Where'd you run off to?
Nowhere, really.
Just wandered around.
I see.
[TSUKIMOTO] Have you been
waiting this whole time?
I've told you
a million times,
a coach's job only has meaning
when he's got
an athlete to train.
But next time you
pull a stunt like that,
I am gonna smack ya.
Are we clear, Mr. Tsukimoto?
Yes.
Yes, my coach.
Beautiful.
Music to my ears.
Well good morning,
Mr. Tsukimoto.
Hey, good morning, Coach.
What's up?
Lovely weather today, yeah?
I guess.
It's gotta be
a bummer for ya,
spending your Valentine's Day
training with an old geezer.
No, not really.
You don't mind? At all?
Nah.
Whaddya say,
Mr. Tsukimoto?
Wanna go on a date?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Uhh...
[KOIZUMI]
With me.
[MATAKI SALESMAN]
Hey, Hikaru.
We're closing down the store,
so go ahead and take some stuff.
On the house.
[OTA]
I couldn't!
[MATAKI SALESMAN]
You play ping-pong, don'tcha?
[OTA]
Whoa, these are three-star!
Badass!
[MATAKI SALESMAN]
You like 'em? Take 'em.
[OTA] Thanks, but I
wanna pay you for them.
[MATAKI SALESMAN]
Don't be silly.
Everyone's gotta switch over
to plastic balls now, anyway.
I heard you haven't
been able to practice
as much as you'd like, so I
bought a ping-pong robot.
It's the latest,
most advanced model!
I've already loaded it up with
as much data as I could find
on Kazama from Kaio.
Please, use it as
a sparring partner.
[KONG]
Thank you.
[singing bowl ringing]
[TAKU]
Morning. Happy birthday.
[YURIE]
Aw, how sweet.
And for you.
Well, you've sure
been busy already.
[YURIE]
Somethin' to drink?
[TAKU]
Coffee. Plain black.
[YURIE] Oh, why'd I have to
be born on Valentine's Day?
Sorry 'bout that.
[YURIE] I always wind up giving
other people stuff all day
and nobody ever
remembers my birthday!
An' it's the same
day Nori died, too.
[YURIE] Here you go,
nice and bitter.
Was Uncle Norio unpopular?
[TAKU] He was a great
table tennis coach.
Some of the kids he taught
are still playing
as adults today.
Ryuichi's style is a lot
like Nori's, actually.
[YURIE] Why's Grampa so hard
on him all the time, though?
Well, to be fair,
the old man's always
been hard on himself, too.
[YURIE] You know, Ryu
never even calls Aunt Emiko.
[TAKU]
He promised your grandfather
he'd only contact her
on days of remembrance.
[YURIE] Yeah, but does
he have to do everything
Grampa tells him to?
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Taku, stop crying.
Boys should never let
anyone see them cry.
Never show weakness!
People will only
take advantage of you!
After your grandfather
took responsibility
for all Nori's
business failures,
our relatives shunned
Nori's branch of the family
out of embarrassment.
Frankly, it went
beyond what was fair.
Of course,
once Grampa saw that Ryuichi
had a knack for table tennis,
his attitude changed,
and as Ryuichi kept winning,
the family had no choice
but to embrace him.
Now that boy is trying
to carry his family,
our school, and even
Poseidon on his shoulders.
Well, that's not for me!
I want to do something
else with my life,
like arrange flowers.
And I'm gonna study in London.
We don't have
that kind of money!
I'd have to ask
your Grampa for help.
No, I don't want his money.
I'll manage myself somehow.
He may be overly
strict and a bit scary,
but he does know
what he's doing.
He's a very shrewd businessman
with great instincts.
I mean, it never even
would've occurred to me
to sell mats and
shoes the way he does.
[YURIE]
So what?
[KAIO PLAYERS]
One!
--Two!
--[SANADA] Kazama.
--Three!
--Do you even know what
today is?
Did you know that ever
since you told Yurie
not to come to our games,
she's been showing up
anyway, in disguise?
[KAIO PLAYERS]
One!
--Two!
--[SANADA] Look, she's here!
And she wants to
give you chocolate!
--Three! Four!
--What are you doing? Go to her!
--One!
--And now she's gone!
--Two!
--What is wrong with you?
[SANADA]
Wait! Hold on!
Hi.
Um, hello, Miss Yurie.
I'm a teammate of Kazama's.
Masayuki Sanada, Kaio Table
Tennis Club, second year!
I've been watching
you from afar!
Happy birthday!
I got these flowers for you!
Aw, really?
Ooh, I love Casablancas!
Thank you!
[SANADA] I am painfully
aware that you like Kazama.
I only wish for you to know
who I am and that I exist.
You are quite beautiful, Miss!
Here, you can have this.
[SANADA]
Thank you!
Later, guy!
[SANADA]
This is mine now, Kazama.
Whatcha gonna do about it?
Whatcha gonna do,
table tennis freak?
I'm gonna
make her mine, too.
I'm gonna beat you.
And take your girl.
You okay with that?
What's wrong,
Mr. Tsukimoto?
Isn't this a blast?
People usually laugh
when they have fun!
Hahaha!
[TSUKIMOTO] Yeah, I'll
let you know when that happens!
Hahahaha!
Hey, you just made a joke!
[TSUKIMOTO] Are you really
having a good time here, Coach?
[KOIZUMI]
Here ya go.
This oughta settle
your stomach some.
God, I hope so. Thank you.
Hey, Coach?
[KOIZUMI]
Yeah, what's up?
[TSUKIMOTO] Can I get Butterfly
Jo to tell me his story?
Yeah, that's what they
used to call me back then.
They said I
played so gracefully,
I looked like a butterfly.
No one could touch me
'cause I was the only one
who could play both
forehand and backhand.
Made me invincible, they said.
I was so young then.
At the time,
folks were heralding me
as the rising star
of Japanese table tennis.
Everyone just took for
granted I'd represent Japan
at the world championships.
But then I lost
in the qualifier.
My opponent was this
guy I'd played with
for almost my whole life.
He was damn good too,
at least until...
...the doc told him
he'd torn a knee ligament
and it'd take six months
to fully recover.
[TSUKIMOTO] He didn't
withdraw from the competition?
[KOIZUMI]
I certainly would have.
But he wasn't me;
this guy simply
refused to give up.
He ignored all the voices
telling him not
to play that day.
Someone injured like that
y'coulda served
deep to the forehand,
then switched to
his backhand side.
Do ya think you
could've done that?
Rubbed salt in an
old friend's wound?
Used a strategy that might've
ended his career for good?
Could you really
have done that?
I made sure he
only had to focus
on his forehand side.
I self-destructed,
and I never played in
another big match again.
Meanwhile, the
public celebrated him
for toughing it out and
playing through his injury.
He rose through the
ranks to worldwide fame.
Now he's President of Kaio
Academy and oversees Poseidon.
Name's Ryu Kazama.
But I need to make one thing
perfectly clear to you, okay?
I'm not using you as some
kind of tool for revenge.
All I've ever wanted
is to show you where talent
like yours can take you.
And help to get you
to that place.
Yeah, I know.
I get it.
I do.
Goodness!
Is that really my Peco
making those drives?
And playing reverse-penhold
backhand, to boot?
Yup!
Back when he was younger,
he always made drives
with inverted rubber, right?
[TAMURA] Yeah 'cause
even at that age,
he was playin'
at the adult table.
When I remembered that
and had him try it,
he got it right away!
When he's facing
stronger opponents,
he tends to get pushed
away from the table,
so he'll be much better off
if he can add drives
to his arsenal!
Teachin' him RPB
was a bit of a last resort
since his backhand
wasn't improving,
but it just clicked for him!
I get what you
see in him now, Mom!
He's got talent!
Most players can't pull off
that kinda sudden switch
in style, but he can!
Peco's got this
sponge-like ability
to absorb new skills
and master 'em in no time!
That's a pretty
major renovation project.
Sure you won't
screw up the whole skyline
with all these changes?
Yeah.
His speed's still his
greatest advantage, I know!
He should play close.
There's gotta be a
style that's a better fit
for a guy like him.
I'll keep thinking.
Those are Peco's
brothers over there.
The kids all have the same face.
It's kinda creepy.
Their mom came to visit,
and damned if she doesn't
have the same face, too!
Now that Peco's living here,
a constant stream of relatives
have been dropping off
food and clothes for him.
[TAMURA] Well, I sure hope
the one practicing there
is the real Peco.
[MICHIO]
Huh?
[NATIONAL TRAINING
PLAYERS] One! Two! Three!
[counting continues]
[TAMURA]
It's heavy.
[MICHIO] Yeah.
It has two rubbers!
You oughta
swap the blade out
for a carbon one
that's under seventy grams.
You got it, Mom!
And what's goin'
on with that bandage
around his right knee?
It worries me.
He's wrapping
it 'cause he says
it's been feeling
a little off lately.
He swears
it's nothing serious,
but it's too soon to be sure.
Well, keep an eye on it,
and don't forget for a second.
He's still just a dumb teenager.
[MICHIO]
Got it!
[TAMURA]
All right, I'm off.
[MICHIO]
Thank you, Mom!
[TAMURA]
See ya later, Peco.
Keep working hard and do
what your coach tells you to.
What, you're leaving already?
You don't wanna stick around
and watch me some more?
[TAMURA]
Aw, dry those tears, kid.
I still love ya.
[HOSHINO]
Come on, Old Lady,
you can't toy with a
boy's heart like that!
These balls aren't
half-bad. Nice work.
Oh yeah?
I'm glad to hear it!
Honestly, I thought you'd
forgotten all about 'em.
Well, Coach is usually
the one in charge of equipment.
I wanna test these guys out.
Let's play a round.
Wouldn't you rather
play the old man?
I mean, I'm not
even dressed for it.
[TSUKIMOTO]
A casual game.
[TSUKIMOTO] They really do
feel completely different.
[OTA]
You think?
Much better.
Yeah, I guess so.
[TSUKIMOTO] I'm gonna
add a little spin now.
[OTA]
Go ahead!
[TSUKIMOTO]
These are great.
Huge improvement
over the old ones.
[TSUKIMOTO]
See?