[MRS. KOIZUMI]
Tsukimoto?
It is Tsukimoto, isn't it?
Are you here to pay my
husband a get-well visit?
Oh, how thoughtful.
They say he
overworked his muscles.
I think he forgets
he's over seventy now!
Come on inside.
I'm sure he'll be
just thrilled to see you.
Uh, no, that's okay.
As long as he's all right,
then I think I'm just gonna go.
[MRS. KOIZUMI] Nonsense!
I'm making dinner. Join us.
[TSUKIMOTO] Thanks, but I
don't really like eating
at other people's houses.
Ah. Perfectly understandable.
Poor boy, you must
have it so rough
with that old man always
giving you such a hard time.
Yeah.
He can be a real
pain in the rear.
Well you're not big
on tact, that's for sure.
Sorry.
No, it's refreshing.
Come see us again
sometime, will ya?
All right. I will.
Look forward to it!
He's adorable.
And such clear eyes.
Well that boy's gonna
become a monster before long.
He's about ready to
burst out of his cocoon.
Just needs a hard-ass
old Ping-Pong coach
to give him a
little push, is all.
[KAIO PRESIDENT] I'm counting on
you to lead us to victory again,
Ryuichi.
For in triumph, we find truth.
Your school needs
you to prevail,
to demonstrate to the world
this institution's supreme
quality in all fields.
[KAZAMA]
Yes, sir!
Though I have some concerns
about the team competition.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Whatever it takes, son;
patch any gaps
in our arsenal!
[KAZAMA] I do have my eye on
a chopper from Katase High.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Katase?
One of Koizumi's, huh?
And this chopper's that good?
I don't know yet, sir.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
If he is, recruit him.
I trust you and Taku
can handle this.
[KAZAMA]
Yes, sir!
Any compromise
is like cutting
off your own arm.
Remember, if we lose,
it's entirely on you.
Yes, sir!
Yeah!
Come back in
three hundred years.
Maybe then you can beat me.
So Koizumi's
working with Smile, eh?
Huh.
I do not like that.
Not a bit.
[MIC CHECK GUY 3A]
Testing mic check.
[MALE PLAYER 3A]
Hey, is that Kaio?
[MALE PLAYER 3B]
Aw, they're here?
[MALE PLAYER 3C] Yeah,
d'ya think they'd no-show?
[MALE PLAYER 3D]
Whoa, check out their heads.
Dammit, Mister Tsukimoto,
where are you?
[n Chinese]
What's wrong, Wenge?
Homesick?
[in Chinese]
Heh, you could say that.
[HOSHINO] So, how's
your bracket looking?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Sucky.
I've got Kong Wenge
in my third match.
Oh, man.
That really does suck.
What's yours like?
Meh, I got a
pretty tough match
in the quarterfinals.
but if I can beat him,
then I'm in the top four
and off to nationals.
Ah.
Speak of the nuisance,
he's coming this way.
Oh, Peco.
Whoops, sorry.
Guess I didn't see
you there, pipsqueak.
'Scuse me?
Should I know who you are?
Y'talk a big game
for a middling player
from a second-rate school.
Least I'm not an
anchor dragging down my team!
Actually, they
just bumped me up
to the varsity squad.
[HOSHINO]
No way!
[TAKU]
Sakuma!
Team meeting!
On the bus!
[SAKUMA]
Yes, sir!
Hey, Smile, you're still taggin'
along with this whiny loser
wherever he goes?
Well, say hi to
the old lady for me.
Yeah, I will.
[SAKUMA]
And Peco!
Don't forget to bring
tissues to our match!
You always sob like
a baby when you lose!
Shut up or I'll
smash your glasses!
Kaio's Varsity squad, huh?
[TAKU]
You know those guys?
[SAKUMA]
Yes sir.
We used to hang out at
the same dojo as kids.
Um, sir, I haven't seen
Kazama around in a while.
[TAKU]
He's in the john.
Don't worry about it.
[SAKUMA]
The john?
Someday, you'll
understand just how tough
this all is for him.
[KONG, in Chinese] I can't
believe I have to play them.
They're like
kids messing around.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Get changed, Wenge.
You're up soon.
[KONG, in Chinese]
You wanna play instead?
You could win.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
You're not a spectator here.
Play seriously.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Ni hao.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
It's that boy.
I'll look into him.
[in Chinese] Suddenly
I feel like there's some hope.
[MALE STUDENT 3A] Hey,
isn't that Kong over there?
[MALE STUDENT 3B]
Didn't think he'd be so emo.
[MALE STUDENT 3C] C'mon, Mister
Bigtime, show us what you got!
[MALE STUDENT 3D] Dude, he
can't understand a word you say.
[MALE STUDENT 3A]
Yo, China!
Go back where you came from!
[KAZAMA]
Knock it off! Now!
Treating our guest
with anything but respect
will not be tolerated.
[MALE STUDENT 3B]
Who's the buzzkill?
[MALE STUDENT 3C]
Shh!
I'm Kazama, from Kaio.
Can we talk for a minute?
I thought Kaio was
supposed to be in a meeting
right now.
Is that a no?
You do not try to hide
how you're feeling, do you?
[MALE STUDENT 3A]
Whoa, awesome drive.
[MALE STUDENT 3B]
It's going dead sideways!
[MALE UMPIRE 3A]
Eleven-love.
Game goes to Kong.
[crowd cheering]
[MALE STUDENT 3C] Ouch,
that dude from Johoku
didn't score a single point!
Facing such a weak opponent,
it's almost impossible to judge
just how good Kong really is.
It's too much.
Not cool.
He didn't have to
embarrass him like that.
Not easy to bounce back
from that kind of defeat.
How very sensitive of you.
It's not sensitivity.
What then, confidence?
[KONG, in Chinese]
Yes!
[crowd cheering]
[KAZAMA] Kong knows
better than any of us
the agony that can come
from failing at table tennis.
His whole life was upended
when he was dropped from
the Chinese National Team.
Bet havin' to play here
on our little island
is the last thing he wants
to be doin' right now.
At least if he conquers Japan,
he'll have a shot at a
comeback in his home country.
But if he loses,
forget about China.
He probably won't even be
able to stick around here.
Which means his career
is pretty much over.
Been meanin' to tell ya.
I don't like the way
you play the game.
Your technique is
flawless, I admit.
However, it absolutely
disgusts me how you always take
your opponent's
feelings into account.
That there tells me you're
not fit to hold a paddle.
Makes me physically sick.
Well, I can't say
it feels great
to be crapped on so bluntly.
Kazama. Time to go.
Yeah. I'm comin'.
[MALE UMPIRE 3A]
Match goes to Kong.
[MURATA]
Damn it.
[MALE STUDENT 3B]
I kinda wanna go home now.
[MALE STUDENT 3A] Murata
didn't even last ten minutes!
[MALE STUDENT 3D]
Poor guy.
Hey, I need you
to listen for a sec.
You have to promise me
that you're not gonna
hold back in there.
It's a bad habit you've got.
Don't worry, sir, I plan to win.
No holding back.
So how much should I win by?
Two points? Ten?
Total skunk?
Whatever you want.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Oh, I know.
Since Kong won his
match in ten minutes,
how about I
get it done in five?
What's gotten into you, son?
Nothin', I just
wanna win, is all.
Is that so wrong?
Oh, no.
Music to my ears.
[SAKUMA] Dude, that
was pretty harsh of you
with Tsukimoto back there.
Now, don't get me wrong,
I think it'll do him some good.
He's always been
a stuck-up little--
[KAZAMA] You seem to know
this dude pretty well.
Any ideas on how to
get him to join our team?
Next year's gonna be rough
if I'm the only
strong player we've got.
[KAZAMA]
Hey, Kong, what's up?
Ni hao, ni hao!
[in Chinese]
Come on, Wenge, that was Kazama!
I hate his type.
[SAKUMA]
Yeah, just ignore us!
Real nice, jerk!
[EGAMI]
Tsukimoto of Katase High.
Here.
Yeah.
[EGAMI]
Never heard of him.
Looks like he's a
decent chopper, though.
Let's have fun.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Okay.
[EGAMI] Well, this
is my last tournament.
Hope third time's the charm.
I can't lose to some first-year.
[MALE UMPIRE 3B]
Ready!
[EGAMI] Man, I really
wanna make it to Nationals.
He's a chopper, so I guess
I'll serve short to his fore
to check out
his defensive skills.
If his return is weak,
I'll send a third ball attack
to the back and then...
Ah, I'll figure it out.
[MALE UMPIRE 3B]
Love-one.
He's playing
an offensive game?
Think he's gonna
stay so close to the table?
[in Chinese]
Is he conserving energy?
He's got a lot of confidence.
[EGAMI]
Tryin' to get under my skin.
Does he think I'm weak?
That he can wrap this up quick
without bothering to chop?
I'm insulted.
And a little hurt.
But his rubber's not
designed for offense.
He won't pull that stunt again!
[MALE UMPIRE 3B]
Love-two.
[EGAMI]
Aw, it's hopeless.
[in Chinese]
We know who will win this.
He scored on a return?
Are you kiddin' me?
This isn't table tennis.
[EGAMI] Why must life
always be so cruel?
Oh well, at least I stuck with
this longer than most things.
Put in three solid,
gloomy years.
Maybe I'll just
go to the beach.
That sounds nice.
[MALE UMPIRE 3B]
Match goes to Tsukimoto.
Dude's been
holdin' out on us.
Can't believe he's
had that up his sleeve
this whole time!
That was some sloppy offense.
Had to unwind.
What, you couldn't
have found another way?
Table tennis to kill time,
and offensive play to unwind.
It's stupid to stake
your life on table tennis.
I just don't get it.
It's revolting.
[in Chinese] He's
Makoto Tsukimoto, a first-year.
[in Chinese]
When do I dance with him?
[in Chinese] The third round,
barring any surprises.
[in Chinese]
The one after next, then.
[EGAMI]
Yeah.
Beach sounds good.
[HOSHINO]
I love Gari Gari Kuns.
Even with these new
stew-flavored ones,
they still have that
crunchy candy center
they've always had.
Way too many snack foods
are losing sight of
themselves these days!
Damn, it's hot this summer!
I still think it's important
for you to go
through with this.
Naw, screw that noise!
I'll still have my pride!
Dropping out's
more shameful than losing.
But Chinese players are
all, like, ridiculously good!
Just 'cause he's Chinese
doesn't automatically
make him good.
You know that's nothing
but a ridiculous stereotype.
Besides, Po, I like it
when a guy takes a risk
knowing he could fail.
Piiko!
[PIIKO]
Anyway, Mister Provincial Team's
a washed-up loser now.
[PO]
Washed-up?
[PIIKO]
You could actually win this.
[PO]
I could?
[MALE UMPIRE 3C]
Game!
Match goes to Kong.
[PO]
She was...
[PIIKO]
...so wrong.
Yeah!
[TAKU]
Good work.
Thank you.
[humming]
[HOSHINO]
You seem pretty confident.
That why you're not using
your strongest move out there?
What, does it bother you?
Maybe.
Offensive play's kinda
my thing, you know.
Oh it is, huh?
Then you prob'ly shoulda
put your name on it.
Akuma's not the same as
when we were kids at Tamura.
You should be careful with him.
I'm not worried.
I could beat that
clown in my sleep.
Good luck.
Well aren't you
a grump today.
What crawled up your butt?
Peco, do you believe in heroes?
Like if you're in real trouble,
a hero'll come
along and save you?
No matter how bad the trouble
is or how deep you're in it?
Ha! You're just
messin' with me, right?
You been readin' too much manga.
[TSUKIMOTO]
I used to believe.
For a very long time,
I was waiting for him to come.
Whatever, just quit
changing your playing style
at random.
It's a bad habit to get in.
[KOIZUMI]
Play him with this racket.
Um, Coach, this one
has long pips-out.
Oh, really?
I hadn't noticed.
I'm not skilled enough yet.
Just give it a go.
But...
I'm playing Kong.
All the better, really.
Good.
[in Chinese]
I'm keyed up.
I haven't felt
that way in a while.
[in Chinese] Just
play it like any other game.
[in Chinese] I kind of
like the feeling, actually.
Tsukimoto and Kong are up now.
Come n' watch.
Thanks.
Hey, so uh, do you
mind if I ask you something?
[KAZAMA]
Huh?
Can't help notice, you're
interested in Tsukimoto.
But why?
The answer to that one's
a little complicated.
Turns out, talent is a gift
that doesn't always wind up
going to the people
who actually want it.
[humming]
Don't hold back.
Alright, Kong?
Because I don't suck.
[KONG, in Chinese] This is the
best you can do after all?
[in Chinese]
Yes!
[KONG, in Chinese]
Blame your environment.
You have no rival,
no master, no pressure!
You'll rust in this
hothouse you live in.
Just like an old bike
tossed in the river.
However,
I have someplace to go back to!
A bountiful country!
[MALE UMPIRE 3D]
Fault!
Game goes to Kong!
So even our ace
can't hold his own
against the Chinese.
[OTA]
Pretty much.
[in Chinese] Wenge, your
plays are getting rough.
[in Chinese] He's nothing.
He can barely return the ball.
[CHINESE COACH]
But he's--
[KONG, in Chinese]
He's no different.
I expected too much.
This is all this country's
players have to offer.
[TSUKIMOTO humming]
[KONG, in Chinese]
Don't worry.
I'll beat him straight up.
[humming continues]
[KONG, in Chinese]
Yes!
[MALE UMPIRE 3D]
Five-seven.
[humming continues]
[MALE UMPIRE 3D]
Six-seven.
[KOIZUMI]
Nice.
Looks like he tricked Kong
into anticipating
all the wrong strokes.
[in Chinese]
He's reading you, Wenge!
Don't shout.
[humming continues]
How 'bout you
actually step up
and compete for
once in your life?
There you go again,
givin' up whenever
you're challenged.
Withdrawing into your shell.
[MALE UMPIRE 3D]
Eleven-seven.
Game goes to Tsukimoto.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Shit!
[humming continues loudly]
Funny thing, talent.
[KOIZUMI]
Perfect!
[MALE STUDENT 3E] I hear China
could really lose this thing!
[MALE STUDENT 3F]
Who's he playing?
[MALE STUDENT 3G]
Some kid from Katase.
He's only a first-year.
No, he can't be.
And yet another
incredible play.
[MALE UMPIRE 3D]
Eleven-six.
Game goes to Tsukimoto.
[in Chinese]
He...
He can read me?
S'like Kong might be
startin' to let his frustration
throw him off his game.
Smile was studyin' 'im
all through that first match,
analyzing him.
He's like a well-oiled machine.
[TAMURA] Smile's finally
living up to his true potential.
No smoking inside.
He can't win, or could he?
[in Chinese]
Shit!
[MALE UMPIRE 3D]
Eight-four.
[MALE STUDENT 3I]
Oh, man.
[MALE STUDENT 3J] It's crazy,
but this could really happen!
[OTA] Tsukimoto is so totally
in the zone right now,
it's almost scary.
[in Chinese]
This is it, Wenge!
Be ready, because if you lose
this match, it's all over!
I thought you were going to
teach the team that dropped you
a lesson!
Quit strutting and get real!
Answer me!
[in Chinese]
Yes, sir.
You're not in Japan
to see the sights, moron!
[KONG, in Chinese]
Yes!
[MALE UMPIRE 3D]
Eight-five.
[SAKUMA]
That return was horrible.
What is he doing?
Well, that's that.
[MALE STUDENT 3K]
How's China doin'?
[MALE STUDENT 3L] Looks
like he'll win after all.
[MALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 3A]
That first-year's lost control.
He's completely
on the defensive now.
[MALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 3B]
That he is.
[FEMALE STUDENT 3A]
Am I nuts,
or was the
first-year kinda cute?
[FEMALE STUDENT 3B]
Oh, definitely!
[MALE STUDENT 3H]
It's all about stamina.
[MALE STUDENT 3M]
Totally.
[MALE UMPIRE 3D]
Match goes to Kong.
[EGAMI]
Well here I am.
At the beach.