[beeping]
[MALE NARRATOR 6A]
The out-of-control robot
demolishes everything
in its path.
Only the legendary hero can
stop this metallic behemoth!
Rise again, hero!
Awaken from your
eternal slumber!
Whoa.
That's awesome!
I read the first, like,
thirteen manga back-to-back!
Yeah, right?
Innit so good?
Man, robots are
cold-blooded killers!
But what hero do they mean?
[BOY 6B] I dunno.
The robot's gone kinda crazy,
but he's really
nice on the inside.
Least he was
before he went nuts.
But like the ad says, the hero's
the only one who can stop him.
[MALE CLUB MEMBER 6A]
From what I hear,
he can totally analyze
his opponents and go after
their weaknesses with
pinpoint accuracy.
But no one can find
any of his weaknesses.
Oh yeah, dude leaves nothing
but ashes in his wake.
[MALE CLUB MEMBER 6A]
You know Manabe? From Kita High?
I heard he took such a beating
he gave up ping-pong for good.
[MALE CLUB MEMBER 6B]
Yeah, even Dragon had to
give this kid props.
Man, I really don't
wanna have to play him.
[OTA grunts]
[MALE UMPIRE 6A]
Match to... Miyasaka.
[MALE FUJI HIGH PLAYER 6A]
Yeah!
[OTA]
Sorry, Tsukimoto.
Why? That's all
I expect outta you.
Damn, that guy pisses
me off sometimes.
[MALE FUJI HIGH PLAYER 6A]
Look! Here he comes!
[MALE FUJI HIGH STUDENT 6A]
Don't let him get to you, bro!
[MIYASAKA]
Battery charged and ready?
Heh. Mister Roboto?
[MIYASAKA grunts]
[MALE FUJI HIGH
PLAYER 6A grunts]
You know, if you ask me...
With all these trendy new,
over-priced, super-fancy,
extra-dark chocolates,
they've made people forget
the true pleasure that comes
from biting into a good ol'
hundred-yen candy bar!
Tell it to the Consumer Affairs
Center and leave me alone.
What are you even
doing here, kid?
I thought you quit ping-pong.
Happiest damn day of my life.
Oh, I'm just here to volunteer.
Y'know, do a little eldercare.
And I'm not after the
chocolate manufacturers.
My beef's with the consumers
who keep buying all
that swanky crap!
[TAMURA] Go home.
[KAIO PRESIDENT] Here it is,
our latest product.
The world's first shoe specially
designed for those mats
they use in international
competitions.
Now, of course, we rarely
play on mats here in Japan,
but overseas this is bound to be
next year's top-selling item.
[MALE DIRECTOR 6A]
All right, everybody,
let's do a quick run-through.
Mister Kazama, can I have you
do some side-to-side footwork
while you play, and then look
right over here at the end?
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Two!
[SANADA]
I can't hear you!
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Three!
Four!
Five!
[NEKOTA] Kazama's playing
hooky again today?
[SANADA]
Don't worry about it.
Yeah well, without you here,
this team woulda
fallen apart by now.
He's a busy guy.
Cut him some slack.
[NEKOTA] We'd be better off
if you were captain.
Just sayin'.
[TSUKIMOTO] Practice'd
be a lot more effective
if only the best players
got to use the tables,
which in turn would
make our team stronger.
So what part of that
am I wrong about?
No, Tsukimoto,
you're not "wrong,"
you're just being
a colossal asshole!
Now let's talk about
these shoddy balls.
[TAKAMURA]
Jeez, what now?
[TSUKIMOTO] I thought I told
you guys to replace them
with the harder ones
that are more uniform.
Oh. Yeah, yeah. I'll go
order 'em right now. Done.
[TSUKIMOTO] That's what
you said last week.
Tsukimoto!
Hey.
Hello, everybody.
Are we all here today?
All right, Mister Tsukimoto,
you're with me.
Let's run.
Fine.
Yeah, that's right! Run!
And don't come back,
you ping-pong ding-dong.
You gotta try not to be
so hard on Captain Ota.
Give him a break, 'uh?
[TSUKIMOTO] All I want is
for him to do his job.
Is that too much to ask?
You know, his job's not
as easy as you might think
and he's doing the
best he can at it.
Are you saying
I'm being selfish?
No...
That's not it.
Yeah, no, I don't know
anything about that.
[HAMA-CHON]
Aw come on dude,
it's all anyone's
been talking about.
Kaio Academy's gonna try and
poach Tsukimoto from our team.
You know more than me.
[HAMA-CHON] But what happens
to us if he leaves?
Heh. Throw a party!
C'mon, don't be mean.
Way I see it, a weirdo like
him never even shoulda
been here in the first place.
Yeah, n' it drives me nuts
how he looks down on all of us.
[phone rings]
[OTA] Hello, thank you for
calling Ota Appliances.
Okay.
You say your favorite show
comes on at seven tonight?
Might be cutting it close,
but I can try to have
it working by then.
Sorry dudes!
Gotta split.
No sweat.
Glad business is good.
[KOIZUMI]
All right. Let's rest.
But I don't need a break.
[KOIZUMI]
Yeah, well, I do, so.
I am over seventy, you know.
I heard that kid
from Kaio up and quit.
What was his name again? Sakuma?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Was only a matter of time.
He would've learned his
limits sooner or later.
[KOIZUMI] Hm.
[TSUKIMOTO 'Scuse me, but, would
you mind not smoking in here?
[KOIZUMI] Hm? Ah.
Yeah, old habit.
[TSUKIMOTO] I'm sorry.
Nah, don't be.
[YAMADA]
Hey, Captain!
Hey yourself, Captain!
[YAMADA] I can always spot you
from a mile away with that hair.
[OTA] Ha, yeah.
I'm just on my way home
from helping my parents.
So, uh, Tsukimoto's
not really fitting in.
That's because he's so good.
Makes sense he sticks out.
[OTA] I guess.
[YAMADA] Anyone looking to
go career with table tennis
is never gonna mesh with
guys like you and me.
We're just in it to make
high school more fun.
Well, hang in there, man.
I gotta get to cram school.
[OTA] Huh.
[water splashes]
[door opens, closes]
[YURIE]
I got some wild lilies!
Aren't they nice?
Gonna get pollen on you.
[YURIE]
Oh, so what!
Hey, didn't your folks used to
be in the florist business?
Way back when?
Wasn't much of a business.
Dad had no head for it.
[YURIE] Casablanca
lilies are pretty,
but mountain lilies
are by far the best.
Only certain flowers
make good decorations.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Having a dream requires talent.
Those without talent are doomed
to fail and should walk away.
[YURIE] You know, your dad was
always kind of a hero to me.
For doing what he loved.
Heroes don't exist.
They're a childish dream.
All that exists is reality,
and those who can't
adapt lose in the end.
[YURIE] Oh, please.
You're a hero.
To Aunt Emiko, at least.
[YURIE] Hey, let's plan to
see the lights at Enoshima
on Christmas Eve!
It'll be a fun break.
I'll ask again when
it gets closer!
[door closes]
[KAIO PRESIDENT] Chinese players
begin practicing on mats
at a very early age.
All the major international
championships are held on mats.
So we here at Kaio Academy now
have mats in our practice hall!
And why is that?
Because Kaio is a
world-class institution!
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
I'm providing each of you
with the world's first shoe
designed for mat-play!
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Yes, sir! Thank you, sir!
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Thank me by winning,
'cause that's what they're for!
Win! Win! Win!
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
[HOSHINO'S GIRL 6A]
Ugh, I'm starving!
[HOSHINO] We've barely
seen any fish.
But we can grab
some ramen later.
Ramen?! Jeez, cheapskate,
did you even get me
an actual present?
You're empty-handed
on Christmas Eve?
Can't believe I ever
agreed to go out with you!
I'm going home!
Dude, I actually hit it!
You guys saw that, didn't cha?
Any idiot could hit it
after that many tries, idiot.
Hey! That's so not cool, man!
[KOEDA] Yeah, okay,
step aside, idiot, watch this.
Hey, what are you
guys up to there?
That's not practice.
Kong!
Quit goofing around.
How many times have I told you?
You need to practice serving.
You're a million years
from doing this right.
You're exaggerating!
Kimura keep working
on your serve
and you'll be a good
player. Trust me.
Really? Will I be
able to play like you?
No chance.
Eh--
All right.
Break time over!
Now practice,
practice, practice!
[KOEDA]
Ha, ha! He told you!
[in Chinese] Someone keeps
walking by the doorway.
Let's get him to help.
[KONG, in Chinese]
We don't need him.
[in Chinese] Look
how many there are.
This will go faster with help.
You out there!
[in English]
Yes. I'm here.
Pleased to meet you, ma'am!
Ni hao. How may
I be of service?
[KONG'S MOTHER, in Chinese]
Nice to meet you.
[KIMURA, in English]
This is hard.
[KONG'S MOTHER, in Chinese]
You're good at it!
[in English] Oh hey, idiot,
what are you doing?
Oh, we're makin'
wontons, look!
This here's Kong's mother.
[KOEDA] Huh?
You should come
join us, bro.
Nice to meet you.
[KONG'S MOTHER, in Chinese]
Welcome!
[in English]
Need any help?
[TSUJIDO PLAYERS chatter]
[GODA] Hey, you guys,
give us a hand!
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 6A]
Oh, man!
[KIMURA] Whoa!
[KOEDA]
Smells so good!
[IIDA]
This is some spread!
[KONG'S MOTHER]
Merry Christmas, everyone!
[TSUJIDO PLAYERS] Merry
Christmas! Merry Christmas!
[TSUJIDO PLAYERS
chatter and laugh]
The hell's this?
[HOSHINO groans]
[KOIZUMI] All righty,
let's call it a day.
Everybody needs
time off, even you.
Merry Christmas.
Go home and get some rest, okay?
[TSUJIDO PLAYERS cheer]
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 6A] Go Kong!
♪ I watch as my angel drifts off
into the sky on steel wings ♪
♪ Left all alone at this
airport and I can't help ♪
♪ but think of
what I just lost ♪
♪ I held my tongue, and
kept my feelings inside. ♪
♪ I should have begged
her not to go ♪
♪ She would be with be now,
we could snuggle up tight, ♪
♪ and light a fire... ♪
Hey, watch where
you're goin', jerk!
[KONG] ♪ But now I've lost
my only reason to live ♪
♪ Oh, 'tis the season,
misery to give ♪
[KONG/TSUJIDO PLAYERS] ♪ It
hurts so much that I wanna die ♪
♪ When will this
feeling subside? ♪
♪ I'm all alone here
on Christmas Eve, ♪
♪ My heart won't drum
on this silent night ♪
♪ There's no escape from
this winter breeze. ♪
♪ No warmth or
hope left in sight. ♪
♪ They flew off at midnight. ♪
[TSUJIDO PLAYERS
cheer and applaud]
[singing continues
in Japanese]
[song ends]
[horn honks]
[HOSHINO sneezes]
[HOSHINO] Hey.
[APE GUY]
Oh! Mister Peco!
You gotta see this
amazing chopper!
[HOSHINO] Who're you?
[APE GUY] Uh!
Ah, I'm just kidding.
So who's the chopper?
[SAKUMA grunts]
Well, well.
Look who it is.
Who is he?
[TAMURA]
World-class idiot.
[SAKUMA] Heh.
Doin' the walk of shame, huh?
It looks like you're "livin'
large" post-table tennis, Peco.
[HOSHINO chuckles]
So, what did you think
of my chop there?
Not too shabby for a guy who
just taught himself, huh?
Yeah, it's really
something.
Color me impressed.
[SAKUMA] Oh, come on, it was
crap and we both know it.
My chop is so weak
I couldn't even beat
a ten year-old with it.
But I hate livin' with
regrets, so I had to try.
[HOSHINO] Hm.
[SAKUMA] All in, fully prepared
to make a fool of myself.
[TAMURA sighs]
[SAKUMA]
But as it turns out,
a style of play
all about endurance
is definitely not
the right fit for me.
Not all birds were meant to fly.
You got real talent,
you know that, dude?
So don't give up the game.
[HOSHINO]
Who are you anymore?
Heh, heh.
I'm a smart guy, and
when Smile beat me,
well, I did a whole
lot of thinking.
I got kicked off the team,
and then suspended for
beating up those punks. Heh.
And it wasn't long
before I started to believe
what he said about
my lack of talent.
Acceptance was actually
a huge relief.
Let me see clearly.
[HOSHINO]
See what?
The stuff you can only see
when competition's not
clouding your brain.
You've got an unbelievable
gift for table tennis.
I've seen it first-hand.
Ugh, quit being
such a weirdo, man!
You're startin' to creep me out.
You'll never get anywhere
if you keep running!
Sorry, but aren't you the
guy who told me to quit
if I was just gonna coast?
Yeah, 'cause I was
trying to get you not to!
[HOSHINO] Well,
I lost to the guy
who got his ass handed
to him by Smile.
So that's my reality.
[SAKUMA] The reality where
you don't do anything?
How come the only thing
you ever do is run?
I can feel my cells dying.
My reflexes are slowing down.
[SAKUMA] Why would anyone
squander so much talent?!
[HOSHINO] Sure, I was really
good, back in the day.
I mean, it never
even occurred to me
that there could be
anybody better than me!
Hell, I could return the ball
with my eyes closed. No problem!
I was able to fly!
I could jump up
and touch the moon
without so much as
breakin' a sweat!
Didn't think it was "miraculous"
'cause it came so natural!
Yeah, I wanted what you had
with every fiber of my being!
I copied your style,
your paddle, your form!
Literally everything about you!
But no matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't be you!
[MAN 6A]
Ha, ha! Check it out!
[MAN 6B] Raw passion
o' youth right there!
[MAN 6C] Why don't
cha get a room?
Dude, everybody in our class,
we all looked up to you.
To us, you were always...
Peco, you love this
sport more than anyone!
[HOSHINO]
Watch this!
[SAKUMA]
What the--?
K-Kaw!
[HOSHINO] See?
I'm like a bird!
I really can fly!
Damn! This is exactly
what I'm talking about!
[SAKUMA] Really wasn't planning
on an ocean swim today!
Freezing!
[HOSHINO] Yeah, a depressing
sport you gotta play
all cooped up indoors in the
summertime is just not for me.
I mean, who cares where a tiny
little plastic ball goes.
[HOSHINO] Uh oh.
Didn't get enough sleep.
Can't breathe.
Jumping in with
all my clothes on?
Maybe not the best idea.
[gasps]
[HOSHINO]
I'm gonna die out here!
[gasps]
[HOSHINO] Where am I?
Near the Bonin Islands?
Have I passed Iwo Jima?
My body's going numb.
I'm fading.
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)] Everybody
says I'm like a robot.
[HOSHINO]
What's that, Smile?
Speak up a little.
Everybody says
I'm like a robot.
Like, everybody.
[HOSHINO]
Hey don't worry, Smile.
You're gonna--
[TAMURA] Look at you, kid.
You were born to play ping-pong.
[HOSHINO] Really?
You really mean that?
The Olympics, huh?
Uh-huh, that's right.
It's my one dream.
I'll be World Champ!
[HOSHINO] I'll be...
[TSUKIMOTO] Peco, do you
believe in heroes?
[HOSHINO] Seriously?
What's with him?
Grow up.
[dolphin sound]
And even ping-pong is
getting more complicated now.
[HOSHINO] Smile.
I don't want to sacrifice
things I like just to win.
That there is
rookie talk, kid.
[HOSHINO] Old Lady.
[HOSHINO screams]
Iron?
[HOSHINO]
Well, I guess this is it.
I just wanna put
an end to it all.
Go far, far away.
Uh!
Papua?
[SAKUMA] Y'ever run your
mouth off like that again...
...I'll kill you.
Can't believe what a
freakin' moron you are.
Tryin' to kill yourself
in the shallows.
Next time aim for
the open water, huh?
Or stick with ping pong.
Run 'til you puke your guts up.
Swing 'til your palms
are covered in blood.
Won't feel any worse than you
do right now, Mister Hero.
[ping pong sounds]
[HOSHINO] Hm? Old Lady?
Huh.
Old Lady! Old Lady! Old Lady!
[TSUKIMOTO] I don't wanna
see Peco embarrass himself.
Do you believe in heroes?
[door closes]
Old Lady!
This picture here.
Just look!
I think every time
we played back then...
Bring back memories?
Found it when I was going
through some old boxes.
Please, listen.
Spit it out.
You tryin' to propose to me?
Come on.
I'm being serious here!
I'm begging, teach me the whole
sport again from scratch!
"Give a fool your time,
and you'll waste the whole day."
[HOSHINO] Please, I need you to
help me send China packing!
Help turn me into
the King of Ping-Pong!
I still wanna be world champ!
I'm gonna feel like a real
idiot if you waste my time.
So you better be ready.
Love ya, kid.