So, even though I had zipped up,
my fly was still wide open!
[laughter]
[KATASE PLAYER 1A] He tried
telling me, but I was all,
"Shut up, bro,
I'm talking to this girl."
So I totally ignored him!
I was flying free for hours.
Till like fifth period!
[laughter]
[KATASE PLAYER 1B] C'mon, Smile,
don'tcha think that's funny?
Yeah. A riot.
[KATASE PLAYER 1A]
Seriously, dude,
don't you ever smile? Jeez.
[KATASE PLAYER 1B]
Hey, where's Peco?
You got me.
[KATASE PLAYER 1A]
Ota's gonna act all pissy again
if Peco doesn't show.
Yeah, he's harder on us
'cause of you two. It sucks!
[TSUKIMOTO]
That does suck.
Aw, come on, man,
don't be like that.
You're the only one Peco
will listen to--help us out!
All right, First Years!
The rest of the team is waiting!
So quit your
lady-talk and come on!
[KATASE PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
[TSUKIMOTO]
Yes, sir...
[OTA] Step it up, First-Years!
I want to see what you got!
So, Captain Yamada...
What's up, Coach?
That chopper with glasses.
I don't remember him
being on our team.
You've gotta
be kidding me.
That kid's one of the
two strongest players
we've got this year. The other
one's skipping out today.
I was gonna ask you
to get on his case.
Who? Pen-hold grip
with the chili bowl cut?
[YAMADA]
That's him.
If he won't practice, then
why don't we kick him off?
Because we need him
if we wanna win.
Slacker or not,
he's still our ace.
Four-Eyes here's not enough?
Well, like I was saying,
sir, he's way better
than anybody else in here,
but he's no match for Hoshino.
You don't say. Hmm...
Peco's probably over
at the table tennis dojo
next to Odakyu station.
Yeah, so what are
you waiting for?
If you want him then go
yourself. I can draw you a map.
Excuse me?
I'm not Peco's keeper.
It's not my job to get him.
[OTA] Go on talking to us
like that kid, and we'll see
if your underwear
can reach your ears!
I think Mr. Ota's
about to crack.
[YAMADA]
Yeah, well...
He lost his regular spot when
Hoshino and Tsukimoto joined up.
Those two can outplay
all us upperclassmen,
and unfortunately
they know it.
Can't blame Ota.
So you're new to
this club, aren'tcha?
That's right, but I been
playin' for ten years.
Sure I can beat a little
snot-nosed punk like you.
[HOSHINO] If you want,
we can find out.
But only if we
make it interesting.
[APE GUY] She doesn't
let us play for money.
Old Lady, we're gonna
borrow Table Four.
[TAMURA] I don't give
my tables to gamblers.
See?
[HOSHINO] Yeah,
she always says that.
Let's start at a thousand
yen a game, okay?
Around here they call me Peco.
You can call me that too,
but after I beat someone,
they gotta add a "Mister."
In other words, it's about
to be "Mr. Peco," got it?
[TSUKIMOTO hums]
[HOSHINO]
Yeah!
[APE GUY groans]
[HOSHINO]
Oh-ho-ho! Yeah!
[APE GUY groans]
You don't get extra points
for bein' a show off!
That's fine. I'm still
gonna spank ya!
[APE GUY grunts;
PECO laughs]
[TAMURA] Hello, Smile.
I haven't seen you much lately.
Who's he?
Some new guy. He's been
bragging all week
about how highly ranked
he was back in Junior High.
But his game reeks of college
rich-kid if you ask me.
[APE GUY]
You think I'm a joke?
How's the school team?
Havin' fun with it?
I guess so. Game's the
same wherever you play.
The saddest part is you
actually believe that.
Wish you hadn't gone with
that low-level school, Smile.
With your talent, you could have
done a hell of a lot better.
Don't give me
so much credit.
[HOSHINO]
Yeah!
The special treatment.
I hate it.
Anyhow, did you think about my
offer, about teaching the kids?
Can't do it. Those brats are way
too unpredictable. Stupid kids.
[APE GUY]
Gotcha!
[HOSHINO]
Ka-Boom!
[APE GUY]
It didn't bounce.
[HOSHINO] Give it three
hundred years more practice.
You might stand a chance.
A decade of hard work,
just to lose like this?
Hate to break it to ya, but
hard work's for people
without talent. In fact,
after I dominate high school,
I'm gonna play in Europe.
This club's gonna get
a nice boost to its rep
when I'm number one, Old Lady.
You must be pumped!
[TAMURA] That there
is rookie talk, kid.
A seasoned player knows
when to keep his mouth shut.
[TSUKIMOTO] Come to
practice tomorrow, Peco.
[HOSHINO] What are you,
my truant officer now?
Wait, let's play!
I don't care if you
show up or not.
The others asked me
to tell you, so I did.
[TAMURA] Criminy. Must be
exhausting to live like that.
Yeah, I used to think
it was hilarious
when we were kids.
But for high school?
Smile better grow out
of it soon, or people are
gonna think there's actually
something wrong with him.
[APE GUY] Oh, I get it, Smile's
an ironic name. Is he good?
[HOSHINO] Good enough to hang
with me since, like, forever.
So that'd be Mr. Smile
to you, moron.
What's with the permanent
frown anyway, Tsukimoto?
Are you mockin' us? You don't
smile 'cause you think we suck?
Lay off him, Ota.
I try to avoid emotional
extremes. It's too exhausting.
[OTA] Well!
Aren't you Captain Cool?
[TAKAMURA]
Don't act all superior!
[YAMADA]
Guys, I said lay off!
Do what we tell ya,
first-year!
Cheer up!
[HOSHINO]
Wow.
I didn't realize an extra year
breathing outside of the womb
makes you such a big shot!
Shut up, dummy!
That little first-year
is beggin' for a fight.
Did you hear him?
You wanna go? I'll go!
[YAMADA] Come on, Ota!
What are you doing?
It's okay. Settle down.
Just focus on
practice, all right?
[HOSHINO] Yeah, you
definitely need it.
[OTA]
Huh?!
Hey, you lay off too, Hoshino!
Neener, neener, neener.
You know they're
just jealous, right?
Because they'll never
beat you at ping pong.
Keep chugging that stuff and
you'll give yourself diabetes.
Let's ditch this lame-ass
excuse for practice
and go over to Tsujido High.
We can check out China.
What are you talking about?
You mean that Chinese exchange
student they recruited?
What's he got to do with us?
For cryin' out loud, Smile.
Do I gotta spell out
every last thing to you?
[TSUKIMOTO]
What?
You should be chompin'
at the bit to see this guy.
He made a Chinese Province team,
that's like going National here.
[KOIZUMI] Hello, everybody!
Are we ready to train?
[PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
[HOSHINO] Great, Coach is here;
now we have to stick around.
Your fault for
dragging your feet.
Then let's get to it.
Dang, Tsukimoto's
on the defensive.
Hoshino's got
some serious game.
No slacking off,
get back to work, huh?
[PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
Question for you,
Captain Yamada.
Is Mr. Tsukimoto
under the weather today?
No, he didn't say
anything to me. Why?
[KOIZUMI] He looks tentative.
No aggression at all.
[YAMADA] Yeah.
That's probably 'cause
he's playing against Hoshino.
The kid's a pain,
but he's gifted.
Everyone looks silly facing him.
Footwork, backhand, blocks...
He's got the whole package.
Have those two been
friends a long time?
[YAMADA] You know
Tamura Table Tennis?
That dojo by the rail station?
[KOIZUMI]
Yeah, of course.
[YAMADA] Apparently, they both
learned there as kids.
I see.
[YAMADA] I'm looking forward
to this year's high school
championships. Who knows
how far those two can go?
We'll find out soon.
Even the strongest panther
in the wild has to
watch out for lions.
[YAMADA]
What's that mean?
Means there's always
someone better, Captain.
[OTA]
First-years, line up!
[PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
[OTA]
Now look around!
Either your teammates can turn
invisible or they skipped out
on practice. What happened
to Tsukimoto and Hoshino?
I'm sorry, Captain Ota.
They said they wanted
to spy on China. Right?
Yeah. I think they went
over to Tsujido High.
[OTA growls]
[OTA] Meet me
behind the gym, punks.
I'm gonna make you
run so hard you puke.
[HOSHINO] Which gum do you think
makes the biggest bubbles?
Beats me.
[HOSHINO] Bubblicious
is good, obviously,
but Marukawa's not bad either,
especially for the price.
I got more if
you want a piece.
No thanks.
So you think Ota's making
all the other first-years
run laps until they
almost pass out?
Probably.
You're a blast to hang out
with, you know that, Smile?
A real conversationalist.
Is our stop next?
[TSUKIMOTO] Not yet.
The one after.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Is it cold outside?
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
How should I know?
Think about it for yourself.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Ugh.
I wish I at least got to
study abroad in Europe.
Sweden or Germany or someplace.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese] It's
a little late to say that now.
Hurry up, Wenge.
For years, Tsujido High
was a powerhouse
that dominated
Eastern Japan.
But lately we've taken a
big dive in the rankings.
So I wracked my brain,
and now here you are.
I'm no genius, but I'm pretty
happy with this idea.
Recruiting a player like
Kong Wenge will give us
a real shot in the arm.
And with any luck,
he'll show the rest of the boys
how to step up their games, too.
[KONG, in Chinese]
What is this? A folk dance?
He says watching the
Japanese style of play
is most enlightening.
[KONG]
Heh.
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 1A] Coach!
We're gonna go run now.
[in Chinese]
Wenge! It's time to run!
[KONG, in Chinese]
That's a stupid training menu.
My game will be rusty after
a semester in this place.
Mm... Could you
translate that?
He's feeling very jetlagged,
and wants to know
if he could please start his
training tomorrow instead?
Oh! Yes, of course,
what was I thinking?
That's not a problem at all.
Hey. Hold on.
You're just gonna waltz right
into another school's gym?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Well, yeah, sure. Why not?
[HOSHINO] "Why not?"
'Cause maybe they don't want...
Ah, never mind.
[TSUKIMOTO] Those doors,
there, you think?
[in Chinese]
Don't get a big head, Wenge.
Remember, they're paying
for you to be here!
[in Chinese] There's no
problem as long as I win.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
You're certainly confident.
[in Chinese]
You saw them, didn't you?
I could play all-forehand
and still not lose.
I should've given up on
my talent a little sooner.
[HOSHINO]
A Chinese penholder?
Kong Wenge?
[HOSHINO]
Hmm...
Oh, wow, real sticky
top-sheet Chinese rubber.
Maybe China killed the
whole team with his kung fu.
I'm sure they're
just out running.
Ugh. Why is everybody so
obsessed with running?
These are some nice tables.
Hey, check this out. The rest
of their paddles are nice, too.
High-grade rubber with
carbon blade layers.
And their team still sucks!
Well, Wenge's not here.
Let's go home.
[TSUKIMOTO gasps]
[HOSHINO]
Hm?
[TSUKIMOTO]
You're kidding, right?
Gotta kill time till
China gets back.
Besides, I wanna return one
of your chops with this baby.
[sound of ping pong volley]
[in Chinese]
You hear that?
Yeah, that's a good chopper.
[KONG, in Chinese] But the
hitter is controlling the game.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
He has speed.
[KONG]
Mm.
[in Chinese]
His play is slipshod
compared to the chopper's.
[in Chinese]
The chopper seems
to have his hands full just
returning the ball, though.
Is the hitter
getting a high arc?
[in Chinese] No, he's got speed,
but he leaves himself wide open.
The chopper is
losing on purpose.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Why?
[in Chinese] Who knows?
Maybe it's a Japanese thing.
Now let's go inside.
The wind makes it
too hard to hear.
[KOIZUMI]
Hmm...
[KATASE PLAYER 1A] Katase High!
Fight! Fight!...
[OTA] You're slowing down,
punks! Move your butts!
[KOIZUMI] Captain Yamada,
I notice Mr. Tsukimoto's AWOL.
[YAMADA] Apparently
he said something
about spying on
Tsujido High and left.
[KOIZUMI]
What?
[YAMADA] I'm sure it's
just an excuse to skip.
Probably Hoshino's idea.
[OTA] I can't hear ya,
first years!
[KATASE PLAYER 1A]
Katase High! Fight!
[PLAYERS]
Fight! Fight! Fight!
[KOIZUMI] All right, Captain,
why don't you bring them inside?
This isn't the track team.
[YAMADA]
But sir...
[OTA] They need discipline,
or they'll skip out
like Tsukimoto and his pal!
You spoil those two!
[KOIZUMI]
You might be right,
but let them off
the hook for today.
[YAMADA]
But Coach...
[KOIZUMI] It'll be good for
them to learn China's got
more to offer than
noodles and dumplings.
[OTA]
First years! Fall in!
[in Chinese]
That's enough!
Keep playing like that and it'll
become a habit, Four-Eyes!
Hey, China!
[in Chinese] Holding back is
disrespectful to your opponent.
Uh, essentially he's
saying that you--
[in Chinese] No need
to interpret, Coach.
Four-Eyes knows what
I'm talking about. Right?
Oh. Ni hao!
[KONG, in Chinese]
Switch.
[CHINESE COACH] Kong would like
to play, if that's all right.
[KONG, in Chinese] See if
you can return my serves.
[HOSHINO]
Xie xie!
[in Chinese]
Not you.
Wenge, just play him.
[KONG]
Tch.
[HOSHINO]
Nice change of speed.
[HOSHINO] Good arc,
and fast, too. I'll call that
his "Super Drive," product of
four thousand years
of Chinese Empire.
Fine, I like a challenge!
[HOSHINO] Well, well,
here comes again.
His four-thousand-year special.
Gotcha!
Huh?
[HOSHINO] Damn. He's got
a sinking drive, too?
Alright, I'll just go
lower this time.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Am I being punished?
[HOSHINO]
His spin's amazing.
I'll have to angle
my paddle down.
[KONG, in Chinese] I get kicked
off the top team, and then they
toss me in with crap players who
wouldn't make the second team?
[HOSHINO gasps]
[KONG, in Chinese]
Is this Hell?!
I was born in the land of ping
pong, and I think I practiced
more than enough. I got results,
too. I've supported my family.
But I make one little mistake,
And I'm stuck with these people.
Your backhand is weak!
And your forehand!
And your legs!
And your reactions!
Nothing about you
is good enough!
Don't you dare think you can
stand at the same table as me!
Why did I have to come to this
country--to the eastern end
of the Earth?
Now learn how powerless...
and unpolished you are!
[HOSHINO screams]
[TSUKIMOTO] Eleven-love.
The match goes to Kong Wenge.
Can't believe I got skunked.
Actually skunked...
[HOSHINO cries]
[TSUKIMOTO] Crying when you
lose is a bad habit, Peco.
Let's go home.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
You went too far.
[in Chinese]
I showed him reality.
[TSUKIMOTO]
C'mon, stand up.
[in Chinese]
Wait, Four-Eyes.
You, in the glasses.
[in Chinese] Show me
your chop sometime.
Kong says he's very
interested in playing you.
Will you please have
a match with him soon?
It'd just end in defeat.
[in Chinese] He says no,
because it would end in defeat.
[in Chinese]
Whose defeat?
[KONG, in Chinese] Four-Eyes
has zero combativeness.
It's a pity he didn't have
a leader to teach it to him.
Although... maybe it's more
of a pity to believe in
a talent you don't have.
[in Chinese]
Wenge...
[KONG, in Chinese]
Come on. Let's practice.
If there are guys like him here,
maybe I can still be saved.
[TSUKIMOTO hums]
What is that?
Monster Robo.
No, I mean the song.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Is it weird?
Yeah, a little.
Is our stop next?
Not yet.
Still the one after.