The singles qualifiers
for the championship
are coming up!
I want us to go in
there ready to dominate!
Take all four slots
again this year!
--Yeah!
Our bracket's full of
heavyweights like Kong
from Tsujido.
Tsukimoto from Katase.
Guys even better than our
championship opponents!
Do not let your guard down!
Understood?
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Yes sir!
Aw, yeah!
Cold noodles!
Spring has definitely sprung!
I never get tired of
eating at this place.
So many seasonal options!
Yeah, yeah, that's
great, Peco, really,
but how you plan
to graduate high school
when you're always here?
Ah, not a problem.
I calculated the number of
days I can skip and still pass.
You go to Katase, don'tcha?
[HOSHINO]
Mm-hmm.
[KOKUBU] You know a
chopper there named Tsukimoto?
I sure do.
Is he good?
Word is he's won
fifty games in a row.
Is that true?
Yeah sounds about right.
[KOKUBU] I got a little brother
who's on a high school team.
He had to play this
Tsukimoto kid one time.
Said his skills are sick.
Like superhuman good!
In fact, he was so tough,
he made my brother
consider quitting.
[KOKUBU] He said it was
like playing against a robot.
Whoa!
That's the Old Lady?
Damn, she used to be super-hot!
Hey, don't give
Peco any more beer!
I know we got some
juice around here!
So you knew that statue
you took a picture of
when you first got
here was Mom, right?
[HOSHINO]
Ooh, a ping-pong girl!
That's Mister Koizumi.
And there's
Kazama's grandfather.
Kaio's president.
[baby crying]
Whoa, you're right!
[MICHIO]
Aw, it's okay!
Upsy-daisy!
It's kind of a
small world, ain't it?
They were all
childhood friends.
Now eat something
and get to bed!
Oh, by the way,
Mom's pretty worried
about that knee
you got wrapped up.
Can't blame her.
You know, a knee injury
is what made her have
to give up competing.
You swear you're okay, though?
[HOSHINO]
Yup!
[MICHIO]
Well, don't sleep out here.
[YURIE] Jeez, you're
always in the bath.
I heard about Poseidon.
How they're providing mats
for the Tournament Qualifiers
to promote their new
mat-based products.
And your teammates are in on it.
They've got 'em all
wearing these special mat shoes
called "Dragons"
for some reason.
You should play
table tennis for yourself
and no one else.
I'm getting outta here.
And don't give me that face.
Huh, really?
I didn't realize Hoshino was
still playing table tennis.
Well, he is, and since you
didn't do your job with him,
I had to work twice as hard.
Sorry, no smoking in here.
All right.
I'll go ahead and register him
along with the other kids, then.
He's always been oddly popular
with the rest of the team.
Sure they won't mind.
Hell, they might even
throw him a parade.
[KOIZUMI]
Question for you, "madame".
Whaddya think're the odds that
your little chili-bowl brat
could defeat Tsukimoto
if they face off
in the next championship?
Is it even possible?
You're the one who
already wrote him off.
[KOIZUMI] Maybe.
But you didn't answer me.
What am I, a bookie?
I dunno the odds.
You just can't compare
this kid to other players.
It's hard for me to say.
One thing I can
say is, talent-wise.
Hoshino's head and shoulders
above the Kazama kid.
That much I know for sure.
Please.
[KAZAMA]
I will get stronger.
Better than my father.
Better than my grandfather!
Hey, isn't that
Makoto Tsukimoto over there?
Whoa, I think he's right.
That's totally him.
What the hell's he doing?
Is he waiting for someone?
[MALE STUDENT 8D]
Hey, did you see?
That was Tsukimoto from Katase.
[MALE STUDENT 8E] Aw, so
that's what he looks like.
[OTA]
Yo, Tsukimoto!
Dude, you gotta get in here!
It's a totally different
vibe this time!
Kaio's here.
They are so hard-core!
Yeah, but what's up
with the bald heads?
[MALE STUDENT 8F] Man,
I wonder if those dudes'll
take the whole Top
Four again this year.
That'd be incredible.
[MALE STUDENT 8G] I dunno, bro,
I say anything could happen.
For one thing,
there's that Tsukimoto
guy from Katase, right?
Rumor goin' around's
that he's the one whose data
Dragon put into
his practice robots.
[gasping]
[HAMA-CHON]
Aw, crap!
Mats!
[TAKAMURA] The floor's
completely covered in 'em!
Huh, I it does feel
kinda on the slippery side.
Guess the ads are right?
[TAKAMURA]
Keep testin' 'em out!
Ow! It's slippery!
Oh, come on, dude.
You fall down on
every kinda surface.
Klutz.
Hey, you remember
how Kazama said
those special new mat shoes
felt like nothing else
in the world?
That was a TV commercial,
you brainwashed idiot.
They got 'em for
sale outside, right?
[MALE CUSTOMER 8A] Size
twenty-seven-and-a-half, please!
[SALESMAN 8A]
Here you go.
[MALE CUSTOMER 8B]
Twenty-six-and-a-half?
[SALESMAN 8A]
All yours!
[COMMERCIAL NARRATOR 7A]
All around the globe,
ping-pong arenas
are using mats.
They're like nothing else.
[COMMERCIAL NARRATOR 7A]
Step out into the world.
The world's first shoes
made especially for mats!
[MALE CUSTOMER 8C]
I need some over here!
[MALE CUSTOMER 8D]
You got any twenty-eights?
[MALE CUSTOMER 8E] How
'bout twenty-six-and-a-half?
All right,
I just checked out
the tournament board!
[TAMURA]
Mm-hmmm?
I doubt the mats
will make any difference.
Pros don't change shoes
dependin' on if the
floor's bare or not.
These guys're just trying
to drum up business!
[TAMURA]
So then, the board?
Y'seen Smile?
[TAMURA] He's in the
stadium with Koizumi.
S'too bad,
I was hoping I'd get a
chance to say hi to him!
Son.
[MICHIO]
Hmm?
[TAMURA]
The tournament board.
[MICHIO] Hmm.
Well in Round One,
he's got a first-year
who should be a cakewalk.
What? Spit it out.
Heads up, Peco!
Wanna know your
Round Two opponent?
Sure.
[MICHIO]
Kong Wenge!
[in Chinese]
What's wrong, Wenge?
Eh...
[in Chinese]
Homesick?
[KONG chuckles]
[KONG, in Chinese]
Ah, you could say that.
Aw, man.
China's already through
to the second round?
But after him,
it's all gravy.
At least until the semifinal
where you'd be up
against Kazama!
How 'bout Smile?
If you play Smile, it won't
be 'til the final round.
He's got no one
standing in his way,
except maybe Sanada
in Round Three.
Nobody else even has a shot!
[HOSHINO]
Is Sanada good?
He's Kaio's number two guy.
Oh.
[HOSHINO] Well,
thanks for the info.
I'm gonna head down there now.
But why?
There's plenty time
before your match.
Yeah, I know.
Alright!
You go and show 'em
who's boss, then!
Make a name for yourself
out there, Peco!
Figured that might freak
him out at least a little,
but he seems to be taking
it all in stride, huh, Mom?
[TAMURA] Nobody gets to the top
without slaying a few monsters.
Guess he must've
prepared himself for it.
Dammit, this totally blows.
Seriously?
Kill me now.
[pouting]
[in Chinese]
You might not believe this,
but my team is
getting pretty good.
It was like teaching
babies to read and write
from scratch.
Today's singles
matches may be rough,
but they'll go far
in the team events.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
I'll look forward to it.
[KONG, in Chinese]
It's true.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
I trust you, Wenge.
Is the strongest one
still that Ryuichi Kazama?
[KONG, in Chinese]
Yeah.
But there's a threat
to him this year.
You remember
Makoto Tsukimoto, Coach?
[in Chinese]
Ah, the one with the glasses!
[KONG, in Chinese]
It's sure to be a good fight.
I'm not up against them
until the semifinals.
It's the Best Four, then the
national championships for me.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
I look forward to that.
[in Chinese] I want to
beat Kazama just once,
and earn my ticket home.
[in Chinese]
Nice.
I'm sure you can do it.
[SANADA] Wait, you're not
wearing the mat shoes?
No.
The shoes don't make
any difference to me.
It's gonna look pretty
dumb if we all go out there
wearin' these things and the guy
who they're named after doesn't.
I've been wearing
Butterfly shoes
since my days in China
and they work just fine.
We wear the same ones whether
on mats or bare floors.
[KOEDA]
No, really?
We bought these!
Well, good shoes are good
shoes, and that's important.
So it's not a total loss.
[PLAYER 8BB]
Whoa, look!
Kong's not wearing
the mat shoes!
And neither's Dragon!
[PLAYER 8CC]
Kazama isn't?
So you're not stressing
out about the mats?
No.
Why would I be?
But more importantly, Coach,
you don't have any
strategic advice?
No tips?
No sir-ee, none at all.
You're already the best damn
ping-pong player I've ever seen,
Mr. Tsukimoto.
I'm quite confident
in your ability
to pull off a
victory here.
[buzzer]
[crowd cheering]
[MALE SPECTATOR 8A]
Go get him, Kong!
[MALE SPECTATOR 8B]
Knock that Kaio punk out!
[MALE SPECTATOR 8C]
Let's go, Kaio!
[MALE SPECTATOR 8D]
Take Kong down!
[in Chinese]
It's time to dance.
Yes!
[in Chinese]
[MOURI]
Damn it!
They're all drives!
[MOURI]
I don't stand a chance here.
I'm just no match for that guy.
Guess this is what
world-class play is like.
It figures I'd finally
make first string at Kaio
only to have this
be my debut match-up.
[MOURI]
Is it about talent?
Am I gonna get yelled at?
Nah.
The only reason I probably even
made the cut in the first place
was because Kaio's
not what it used to be.
I don't think anyone
expects too much from me.
[MALE UMPIRE 8A]
Eleven-two!
Match goes to Kong!
[crowd cheering]
[MOURI]
Pitiful.
Yo, I did it!
I won!
Thank you for everything, man!
That was only Round One.
Yeah, that may be,
but I was up against
Higashi from Minami High!
Yeah? So what, you dope,
that's nothing.
I just beat a
guy from Kita High!
If you keep practicing
hard like you have been,
you will all
keep improving.
Trust me.
So if I try real hard
and work myself to death,
I'll be able to play
as well as Tsukimoto?
No chance.
[laughing]
Ah, just kidding.
Who knows?
Maybe you've got talent
waiting to burst out.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
We're about to begin Round Two.
All athletes please report
to your assigned tables
immediately.
I remember you from
our little game last year.
[chuckles]
Well, I wouldn't
mind if you erased
that particular memory.
Oh yeah,
I should tell you,
I'm a slightly different
player than I was last time.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Japanese penhold
with a rubber
on the back!
This guy.
Really, it's like I've
been fully remodeled.
So, y'know, fair warning
and everything, Kong!
[MALE UMPIRE 8B]
Game to Tsukimoto.
[TAKU] No word describes that
boy other than "brilliant."
His economy of
movement, his strokes,
his control, and his speed.
He's phenomenal at everything.
Ryuichi?
Huh?
Sorry.
What's the matter?
Table Twelve.
Ah, Kong Wenge.
That's right.
Well watch 'im closely;
you'll definitely be going
up against him later.
I'm not so sure.
Check it.
He's gonna lose the first game.
[MALE UMPIRE 8C]
Out!
Ten-seven, Hoshino.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Shit!
[in Chinese]
Wenge...
Who the hell
is this Hoshino kid?
[KAZAMA]
No idea.
Yeah, Kong's gotta be
gettin' sweaty in
the britches about now.
After all, this is a kid
he managed to skunk
just over a year ago.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Is this really the same guy
from last year?
He's completely different.
That guy didn't have drives.
Is he someone else?
He's fast!
Ugh!
No!
It's him!
He hasn't overcome
his weak backhand side.
Why no RPB shots, then?
Isn't that what
the rubber is for?
Doesn't he have any?
Doesn't he?
[in Chinese]
He doesn't really have
a backhand, Wenge!
Don't let the racket fool you!
He hasn't mastered
the RPB style yet!
[KONG, in Chinese]
I see!
Ni hao!
[KONG, in Chinese]
I see now!
[TAMURA]
There it is.
[MALE UMPIRE 8C]
Eleven-eight.
Game goes to Hoshino!
[MALE SPECTATOR 8E] He actually
took a game from Kong?
[MALE SPECTATOR 8F] That
penholder's using both sides!
[NEKOTA] Go over all the
data we have on this Hoshino.
[MOURI] His backhand was
almost like a forehand.
What is he doing?
I specifically told him to try
that on someone weaker first!
Son.
Bluffs are their most effective
when used against
the best players.
You know this.
Love ya, Peco!
Yeah!
Hey, you there!
Uh, you're in the middle of a
match here, Tsukimoto!
[TSUKIMOTO]
Right.
Sorry about that.
Welcome back, hero.
Nice one.
Well, well.
[MICHIO] He just learned both
the Chiquita and the Miuta!
[TAMURA] That kid is
something else, huh?
He's growing.
Right before our eyes.
This is all just
one big game to him.
See?
He bowls people over.
Whatever it takes
to get to the top.
Honestly, it's
almost frightening.
The most likely
explanation is Kong panicked
and it threw him off his game.
Yeah. But...
Yeah!
[MALE UMPIRE 8C]
Nine-six.
Hoshino leads.
[crowd cheering]
[KONG] Hey, do you remember
how when you first played me,
you couldn't score
even a single point?
You've come a long way.
[HOSHINO] I owe you
a big xie xie, Kong.
Thanks to you crushing me,
I pushed myself to get stronger.
I guess in a way,
it was you who finally
taught me how to fly.
[KAZAMA]
Huh.
Real talent.
What're you doin'
here, Mister Tsukimoto?
Done already?
Yeah.
Well, that sure was fast.
[TSUKIMOTO] You mean
you weren't watching me?
[KOIZUMI]
Course not.
I knew you'd win this round.
[TSUKIMOTO]
But I lost.
Huh?!
[TSUKIMOTO]
Just kidding.
Hoshino?
Yeah.
Your pal's playing a
pretty interesting game.
Driver RPB.
[KOIZUMI] What, you're not
gonna watch the rest of this?
[TSUKIMOTO] Course not,
I know he'll win this round.
[MALE UMPIRE 8C]
Out!
Ten-seven.
Hoshino.
[TAKU]
He's tightening the noose.
[KAZAMA]
Yeah, he is.
[TAMURA]
Atta boy.
[KONG, in Chinese] I wish I'd
at least gotten myself
stuck in Europe.
Sweden or Germany
or someplace.
It's the Best Four,
then the national
championships for me.
Japan, huh.
Go on!
Kick his butt, Kong!
[KONG, in Chinese]
Say hi to Kazama for me.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Got your ticket, Wenge?
[KONG'S MOTHER, in Chinese] I'm
waiting for your return, Wenge.
[MALE UMPIRE 8C]
Match goes to Hoshino!
[HOSHINO (CHILD)] Just call me
whenever you're in a pinch!
Chant these words
three times in your mind!
"The hero appears!
The hero appears!
The hero appears!"
If you do that,
I'll come runnin'.
Whoosh!
Zoom!
All the way from
Planet Ping-Pong!