Aw, you cut yourself?
Where is it at?
Here, on my left knee.
It's bleeding bad.
Eh, that's nothing a little
bit of spit can't fix up.
Huh? What's that?
Sorry, couldn't hear.
How's it taste?
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
It tastes like...iron?
[MALE INTERVIEWER 9A]
S'cuse me, sir.
Are you Japanese?
Oh yeah, I sure am.
Born and raised.
[MALE INTERVIEWER 9A]
So, what were you doing abroad?
A friend of mine and I
had a wedding to go to.
We had a great time!
[EGAMI] I was on an utterly
aimless journey to find myself.
Wandered all over this world,
yet somehow never found a single
place that agreed with me.
[EGAMI laughing]
Oh boy,
ya got that right!
[MALE INTERVIEWER 9A] All right,
thanks for your time.
Hey, when's this gonna air?
[MALE INTERVIEWER 9A]
Friday night at six-thirty.
Be sure to tune in.
Definitely!
I can't wait to see it, yo!
[EGAMI]
They won't use any of me.
Huh.
It's been exactly
one year since that day.
[EGAMI] I've come
a long way since then.
Maybe I'll go check
out some table tennis.
[in Chinese] Sorry I lost after
you came all the way here,
Coach.
[in Chinese]
It's fine.
Upsets like this make
the sport interesting.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Yeah.
That bowl-headed kid
is the real deal,
and I don't say that
just because I lost.
[in Chinese]
I know.
[KONG, in Chinese] Heh, guess I
don't have time to sit and mope.
[KIMURA]
Oh, crap.
I think he saw us.
It's 'cause you stuck
your head out too far, idiot.
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 9A]
Was Wenge crying?
[KONG, in Chinese] I have to
go teach my lost ducklings
how to fly.
[PLAYER 9A]
Hey, didja hear?
Apparently Kong from Tsujido
lost every game in his match!
[PLAYER 9B]
Seriously?
Who was he playing?
[PLAYER 9A]
Some Katase second-year
no one had ever
heard of, named Hoshino.
[PLAYER 9B] Huh, I thought
Tsukimoto was the only one
at that school
that had any game!
Yeah, they sold us
a bunch of lies.
This Hoshino's supposed
to be a powerhouse.
Coach says in the semis,
he might even give Kazama
a run for his money.
That's huge!
If that happens,
Kaio's in trouble.
Yeah, well in
the third round,
Sanada's gotta go
up against Tsukimoto.
Good luck.
Aw, for reals?
That's rough.
It's not gonna
look good for Kaio
if their number two gets
knocked out that early.
[PLAYER 9A]
Yeah, no kiddin'.
But hey, it'd serve 'em right.
Those bald bullies are
way too full o' themselves.
[PLAYER 9A laughs]
Whatever, they're on a
whole other level from us.
[PLAYER 9B]
Y'can say that again!
[KAZAMA (CHILD)]
Wild lilies!
[NORIO]
You'll get pollen on you!
Their pollen is super greasy,
so it's hard to wash off.
Still, your old man loves 'em!
[NORIO]
Birds have it good.
They can get high
above this mountain
and they barely have to try.
Figure they've been watching
our ugly wars and struggles
long before there
were airplanes,
thinking how stupid we are.
I wish I were a bird.
[KAZAMA (CHILD)]
Careful Dad.
That's dangerous!
Dad!
Kazama isn't here.
Uh, no, sir.
[SANADA] Well, I suppose he
doesn't think this match
is worth watching.
Stop it!
Hey, Coach.
Can I ask you
somethin' real quick?
[SANADA] If I win,
do you think there's a chance
he might finally
start to think a little
more highly of us?
Try not to get distracted.
Just focus on
your match, Sanada.
Yes, sir.
Now calling to Court Nine
Tsukimoto, Katase High School
and Sanada, Kaio Academy.
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Fight! Fight! Fight!
[chanting continues]
Oh yeah!
[TAMURA] So, is Eyebrows
there any good, or what?
[MICHIO]
One of the best kids here.
He's overshadowed by Dragon,
but don't
underestimate him.
Sanada is a monster
in his own right.
Top Four at last year's prelim
and Top Sixteen nationwide.
[TAMURA]
A monster, eh?
[HOSHINO]
Ah, no worries.
Smile won't lose to this clown.
Peco!
Where the hell have you been?
I looked all over!
In the crapper.
Don' be crass!
Congrats, kid.
It was nothin'.
[MICHIO]
Crush him, Smile!
Show him who's boss!
[TAMURA] So. You think
your knee's gonna hold up?
Come on, Smile!
You got this!
[TAMURA] I may be old,
kid, but I'm not blind.
[HOSHINO] Thanks for the
concern, but I'm fine.
Really.
[TAMURA]
Okay.
[MICHIO]
He looked this way!
Over here!
Hey, Smile!
Hey!
[SANADA] Gotta say, I'm a
pretty happy guy right now.
Been looking forward to this
for a long time, Tsukimoto...
I'm Sanada from Kaio.
Tsukimoto, Katase High.
Nice to meet you.
[crowd cheering]
[ping pong balls bouncing]
Yes!
[MALE UMPIRE 9A]
Eight-one Sanada!
[SANADA]
Yeah, yeah!
That guy's power
is ridiculous!
Even Smile is helpless
in the face of it!
Wow.
That sounds like it
might be a problem.
Yeah!
[MALE UMPIRE 9A]
Out!
Nine-one!
Wonder if it's finally game over
for our golden boy out there?
[SANADA] Coach and Kazama
speak so highly of this guy,
I was actually kinda nervous.
But in the end...
...he's still just
a Katase shmuck.
Go! Crush 'im!
[KAIO PLAYER 9B]
Yeah!
[KAIO PLAYER 9C]
Go!
[TAKU]
I smell trouble.
[SANADA]
Just watch, Kazama.
I'm gonna win.
This punk you've
been so focused on,
so scared of--
[SANADA]
I'll kick his ass!
[MALE UMPIRE 9A]
Out!
Two-nine.
Tsukimoto!
[SANADA]
You son of a bitch!
[TAKU]
Bah.
[TAKU] Tsukimoto
found Sanada's weakness.
He can't handle a string
of attacks to his middle.
[TAMURA]
He's brutal and merciless.
Do you get it now, Michio?
That's the Smile
Monster's true gift.
[SANADA] So he was just testing
me this whole damn time?
Is that why he scattered
all his shots like that?
What a dick move!
When you mess with Kaio,
we take you down hard!
Here I go.
[SANADA]
Shit!
[SANADA] I can slam
shots at 'im all day,
but as long he keeps
returning 'em like that,
I don't stand a chance!
Net ball!
Eleven-nine.
Game goes to Tsukimoto!
[crowd cheering]
Wow, now that is
a ping-pong player.
He totally turned the tables!
Ha, ha!
He just scored
ten points in a row
on Sanada!
[MALE SPECTATOR 9B]
Unbelievable!
To think Sanada could
go down in the third round!
[KOIZUMI]
Way to go, son.
[SANADA]
What's with this guy?
I can't spot a single weakness.
He's solid no
matter where I attack.
Not to mention, he...
Dang.
Smile's manned up.
[MALE UMPIRE 9A]
Out!
Eleven-two.
Game goes to Tsukimoto!
[crowd cheering]
[SANADA]
Gotta hand it to him.
There was nothing I could do.
He really is as
good as they say.
See why Kazama
wants him so bad.
I was dreaming.
You're the one
who's got real vision
and a spine of
steel, Kazama.
It's you who puts table
tennis and the team first.
I'm a soft, small-minded,
little man compared to you.
With my half-hearted attitude,
there's no way I could
ever compete with you.
I get it now, why
Yurie fell for you.
But I am still Sanada
of Kaio Academy!
So you damn well better
finish what I started, Kazama!
Come on, Muuko,
pick up the pace.
If you don't hurry.
I'll leave you behind!
Hey, look there, Bubu.
I think that that's
a swimming pool.
Can we go check it out?
Please?
[SAKUMA] You wanna swim,
knock yourself out.
I'm going in now.
[MUUKO]
For Pete's sake.
I was just letting you know.
Sheesh!
Hey, are you mad at me?
Bubu, wait.
I'm talking to you!
[laughing]
[SAKUMA]
I could almost cry.
Hey, the
tournament's this way.
Isn't that why we're here?
Where are you going now?
Bathroom.
I'm real sorry to
bother you, but Kazama?
It's Sakuma.
Manabu Sakuma.
[KAZAMA]
Right.
[SAKUMA]
Dang, it's been, what?
About six months
since we last spoke?
[KAZAMA]
Yeah.
How've you been, Sakuma?
[SAKUMA laughing]
What's so funny?
I've been all right.
Good.
So I saw the board.
Sanada faces Tsukimoto
in the third round, right?
Yeah, Sanada's a
top-notch player, no doubt,
but I can't see him even
winnin' one game in that match.
Poor guy.
Bet Smile's the last
person he'd wanna lose to.
The thing is, if you
really wanna win,
you've gotta be willing
to put in all the hard work
to get you there.
You know,
I honestly suspect
that's your actual opinion.
It's everyone's opinion,
'cause it's true.
Now that I've
given up table tennis,
and I've gotten
a little distance...
I think I finally get it.
Why you hide here
before a match.
And why's that?
[SAKUMA] Kazama, who do
you play table tennis for?
I play for
myself, of course.
[SAKUMA] Please,
don't joke about this.
Because if that were true,
then I wouldn't have...
Sorry, it's not my
place to say this stuff.
Just forget I said any of it.
I'll leave you alone.
[KAZAMA]
Sakuma.
Do you resent me?
I sympathize with you.
I don't really expect
you to understand,
but that's how I feel.
I look forward
to you winning.
I know you can do it again.
Thanks.
[MUUKO]
Bubu, is your tummy okay?
[SAKUMA]
It's fine, why?
[MUUKO] You were in
there a really long time!
[SAKUMA]
Wait here a sec.
I'll be right back.
Jeez, what's with you?
Gonna cry a bit.
[KAZAMA]
Hey.
Oh hey, Kazama.
Sanada's, um...
[KAZAMA]
Yeah.
I mean, it was like
something out of a nightmare.
There was no way
I could ever beat 'im.
That kid's just not human.
Ya know Sakuma's
here somewhere.
Did you see him?
Yeah, we talked
for a little bit.
Oh, yeah?
And what'd he have
to say to you?
Not much.
He did ask me who I
play table tennis for.
Yeah, so what
was your answer?
"I play for the
team, of course."
That sounds like
something you'd say.
[crowd cheering]
[MALE SPECTATOR 9C]
Whoa.
[MALE UMPIRE 9B]
Match goes to Kazama!
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
[NEKOTA]
Yes!
[MALE UMPIRE 9C]
Match to Nekota!
[MALE UMPIRE 9D]
Nine-ten, Okano!
Booyah!
You're makin'
rookie mistakes, Peco!
Come on!
You only need to
get one more point!
He's not just dragging
this out for the fun of it
or to make things
more interesting.
If he was operating at
a hundred percent here,
he wouldn't be tired
from a few matches.
His knee's busted.
Pity.
Yeah.
See, he's favorin'
his right leg.
His balance is all outta whack.
Seems he's now paying
the price of our overtraining.
[MALE UMPIRE 9D]
Out!
Match goes to Hoshino!
[crowd cheering]
Peco.
[KOIZUMI] It's dangerous for him
to keep playing like that.
[MALE UMPIRE 9E]
Net!
[NEKOTA]
Crap!
[MALE UMPIRE 9E]
Ten-two. Tsukimoto!
[crowd cheering]
[NEKOTA] He never even
makes the slightest mistake.
Every error is mine.
He never loses his cool,
never gets tired.
His technique is flawless.
Perfectly calculated.
Should I serve now
or would you like more time?
[NEKOTA]
He really is a robot.
Go ahead.
Does he even have blood
running through his veins,
or just circuitry?
[MALE UMPIRE 9E]
Match goes to Tsukimoto!
I think I might cry.
Great job, Tsukimoto!
Super match.
Yeah, thanks, guys.
[OTA]
You were amazing!
Seriously, I was blown away!
Where's Hoshino?
He's not here yet.
Yeah man, his knee.
Doc says it's real bad.
Oh? Is that right?
Yeah.
[TAKAMURA]
Hey, where ya goin'?
Aren't you gonna
stick around, bro?
Support Hoshino?
Hey, buddy!
What is this?
Where the hell's our opponent?
My guy's already warmed up
and now his muscles
are gonna get cold!
How long's he have to wait?
[MALE STAFF 9A]
Sorry, sir!
I'll see what I can do!
So now what?
You wanna practice a bit?
No, don't need to.
Suppose you're right.
This match will probably
get called off anyway.
[HOSHINO]
I feel great, Michio.
They shot me up
with painkillers.
You don't know how serious
a knee injury can get!
You made it to the Top Four,
meaning you can quit now and
still play the championship!
--[HOSHINO] Nah.
--[MICHIO] What?
[MALE STAFF 9A]
'Scuse me, Kaio's wondering--
It's too dangerous!
Be right there!
[MALE STAFF 9A]
So, um...
Just cool your
jets a second, will ya?
I want'cha to
listen good, Peco.
Players your age should
be reckless sometimes.
Occasional lack of
caution can be a virtue.
However, if you truly
want a shot at becoming
a world champion,
you've gotta learn
how to fold when necessary.
Raise the white flag.
I'm not new to this game.
I've been playing pretty
much since I was in diapers.
I've seen plenty of
tough guys burst into tears
after wrecking their knees.
And of course I know about how
a bum knee ended your career,
Old Lady.
So why risk it?
'Cause Smile is calling to me.
[HOSHINO] When we were little,
he got picked on all the time.
Even then, he never smiled.
The other kids gave
him stupid nicknames
like "Robot" and "Golgo."
Because of that, he always
just sat by himself,
and played video games
his dad bought him.
But when I showed him
how to play ping-pong,
the dude
smiled like crazy.
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)] Do you think
I'll ever be like you, Peco?
'Cause I wanna be.
I wanna be just like you.
[HOSHINO]
But I forgot all about it
'til I saw that
photo at the dojo.
I didn't start callin' him
"Smile" because he doesn't.
I called him that
'cause of how he looked
whenever he played Ping-Pong.
[HOSHINO (CHILD)] Just call
me whenever you're in a pinch!
If you do that,
I'll come runnin'.
[HOSHINO] He's been waiting
on me for a long time now.
He's believed in me
since way back when.
The only reason
he stopped smiling...
...is 'cause of me.
I started phoning it in
and my gameplay stunk.
I knew it,
but I pretended not to.
I was scared, so I
just shut everything out.
But now, it's time
for me to go to him.
Michio, hand me my paddle.
[HOSHINO]
Before I face Smile,
I got one more giant
monster to take down!
[TAMURA] Peco.
Who are you playing for?
Is it Smile?
Are you kiddin'?
No way!
I'm the hero of
this story, not him!
And don't you dare forget it!
I love ya, kid.
Get 'em.
[HOSHINO (CHILD)] Chant these
words three times in your mind!
"The hero appears!
The hero appears!
The hero appears!" If you
do that, I'll come runnin'.
[MALE STAFF 9A]
Clear a path, please!
Athlete coming through!
[HOSHINO (CHILD)] All the way
from the planet Ping-Pong!
Yeah!