Hey, Smile, you're
still taggin' along
with this whiny loser
wherever he goes?
Well, say hi to
the old lady for me.
Kaio's varsity squad, huh?
Well, way to go, Akuma.
[CROWD cheering]
[KAZAMA] Any ideas on how
to get him to join our team?
Let me tell you a secret to
spare you all that future pain.
The only way to not
lose is to not fight.
[SAKUMA]
Wait a sec, where's Kazama?
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Are you sure about this, Wenge?
You don't have
to stay here alone.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Well, I'd feel ashamed
to show my
face there, anyway.
Plus, I was hired to beef
up that weak little club,
even if that
wasn't the real goal.
[in English] Hello,
it's good to meet you.
Thank you very much.
[chuckles]
[KONG, in Chinese]
I sound good, right?
The one saving grace is that
Kazama won worldwide, too.
If he'd lost the high
school championship,
I'd have asked a witch
to turn me into a frog.
[CHINESE COACH laughs]
[in Chinese]
I'll miss you, Wenge.
I'll miss you, too.
[REPORTERS shouting]
Hey, Kazama!
Great job at the Youth Olympics!
How's the gold feel?
Can I get a quote, Dragon?
[KAZAMA] I wish we'd done better
in the team and doubles events.
But I'm satisfied with my
win in the singles, at least.
Above all, I'm worried.
My school means more
to me than anything else.
And right now
my school's in trouble.
Let's face it.
The last few years, the
collective strength of our team
has sharply declined.
Kaio Academy used
to be like a fortress.
And if we're going to
be that fortress again,
we need stronger players.
Like Tsukimoto from
Katase High School.
No further comment.
[REPORTERS shouting]
[MALE REPORTER 5C] Isn't that
the girl from those commercials?
[MALE REPORTER 5D]
The Poseidon ones?
[MALE ANCHOR 5A] And that was
our all-too-brief interview
with Ryuichi Kazama,
our very own Youth Olympian,
who just took gold in
the table tennis singles.
We'll be back with
weather, right after this.
[YURIE] All the gear
you need to play!
Come on down today!
Congratulations, Ryu!
You totally killed it!
I've never seen Aunt Emiko
so excited, it was great!
Did you call her yet?
No.
Well you definitely should.
It'd make her super happy.
I hear she's always
showing clippings about you
to her customers.
So home?
Not yet.
I want to stop
by the school first.
Guess there's no
rest for the weary, huh?
There's a great
pancake house nearby.
We could sit down.
[YURIE]
Okay, I get it.
Soon-to-be World Champ
has no time for pancakes.
The whole world revolves around
grampa and his precious school.
[HOSHINO]
Kinda pricey.
[HOSHINO'S GIRL 5A]
What are you talking about?
It's a steal!
That'd cost double
at any decent resort.
[HOSHINO] You sure
we need that stuff?
[HOSHINO'S GIRL 5A] I'll burn
to a crisp in half an hour
without a parasol.
And chairs are a must.
Ugh. You're so cheap.
I'm gonna have sand everywhere.
[HOSHINO'S GIRL 5A]
Can you put my lotion on?
[HOSHINO]
Yeah, in a sec.
[HOSHINO'S GIRL 5A]
Wow. Your screen's ridiculous.
It's completely cracked!
So I hear there's a famous
pancake house nearby.
We should check it out.
Hey mister!
Over here!
[EGAMI]
Yes, sir!
[HOSHINO]
Order for me, will ya?
[HOSHINO'S GIRL 5A]
What?
What can I getcha?
[HOSHINO'S GIRL 5A]
I don't eat that crap.
[EGAMI]
Hm?
Oh well.
I guess the sea doesn't
agree with me, either.
Maybe the mountains, then.
[laughing]
[BEACH MAN 5A]
You ready to return that, sir?
We're about to close.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
You did very well, Ryuichi.
We're going to spend big money
featuring you in
our next ad campaign.
But that was quite
a stunt you pulled today.
And on live TV, no less.
You really think
he's going to transfer?
[KAZAMA]
I'm certain.
He'd have to be a fool not to
realize what we can offer 'im.
Make it happen.
I want Kaio to be
invincible at all costs.
[TAKU]
This is bad, Ryuichi.
You understand that, right?
[KAZAMA]
Yes, sir!
Very sorry sir!
I know you made those
comments to the press
'cause you're concerned
about Kaio's future.
But the guys are
still recovering
from getting thrashed
in the tournament.
How do you think they feel
hearing their captain
only cares about a guy
who's not on our team?
[KAZAMA]
You're right, sir.
I apologize.
So, Kazama was
called into Coach's office?
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
--Yes, sir!
You saw him on TV today?
What he said at the airport?
[KAIO PLAYER 5A]
Yeah.
[NEKOTA] Dude's supposed
to be like a robot.
They say he never smiles.
Yeah his name's
Tsukimoto, right?
Thing is, that
was not a slip up.
It was a completely calculated
move on Kazama's part.
Just watch.
He'll try and get
"Mr. Roboto" on our team.
[NEKOTA]
Probably so, yeah.
[KONG]
Thank you very much, sir.
[panting]
Your pace is dropping!
You gotta pick it up!
Pump those arms!
Harder! Let's go!
Don't let up!
Push through it!
Okay, that's enough!
Come on, walk it off.
Y'don't wanna cramp up.
[KOIZUMI] Ah, Captain
Ota, how's it going?
You boys heading out?
[OTA]
Yessir.
We're callin' it a day,
but I can hang back if
you need help with somethin'.
No, I think we're
good, but thanks.
[OTA] All right.
Later, Coach.
[KOIZUMI]
Nighty night!
Jeez. He's freaking obsessed.
Hey, Ota.
You got plans?
Gotta study for my license.
I need it soon so I can
drive my family's work truck.
Work truck?
Lucky dog.
We gotta get saddled
with college debt.
Dumbass.
It's a small town
appliance store.
That really sound
glamorous to you?
[KOIZUMI]
Your old pal Mr. Chili-bowl
didn't come today, either.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Let's go inside.
It's starting to get cold.
[KOIZUMI]
Mm, I suppose that's fine.
[TSUKIMOTO] Multi-ball
practice is next, right?
[KOIZUMI]
Can't wait!
Move your feet!
That return was weak!
Don't just use your hands!
Put your body into it!
Too slow!
Move your legs with purpose!
Yeah, when it comes
to popsicle brands,
this has gotta be
my all-time fave.
Their company's famous
for their free-wheeling
management style.
And that "black pop"
commercial was pure genius.
They could survive for years
on the success
of their orange cream.
But instead they keep
reinventing themselves
with great new stuff.
Almost didn't recognize you.
You look like burnt toast.
I thought you quit, Hoshino.
I don't see Smile anywhere.
It kinda looks like
you put on some weight.
What? You think so?
Tsukimoto's out running
laps with the old man,
like always.
[OTA] He's on a different
training plan from us.
Dude's coming to
school at five AM.
--Runs 10K every day.
--[KOIZUMI] Go! Go!
Ten kilometers,
you believe that?
He's gotta have three
times the energy we do.
And the old man sets him up
with a crazy number of matches.
I'm telling ya, it's nuts!
[HOSHINO]
Why?
[KOIZUMI]
Hello, everybody.
Are we ready for a
good day of practice?
'Sup!
[TSUKIMOTO]
You've put on some weight.
What, you too?
No, man.
It's just your new glasses.
[TSUKIMOTO] You're eating
too much junk food.
Can't stop now,
it's my signature.
And the smoking?
[HOSHINO]
What?
Now you know how it feels.
He looks down on us all.
That's why he's playin'
in so many matches.
Nobody on our team's good
enough to practice against.
That means the rest of us have
to play schools at his level,
so we don't stand a chance.
His Royal Majesty
the Prince of Ping Pong's
riding the winning
streak highway alone.
No such thing as team spirit
on this club anymore.
He's a one-man army.
We just collect the balls.
You serious?
Sakuma's not here today?
No sir.
He said he was coming
down with a cold,
so he'd spend the day
in his dorm room.
He's got a cold?
Understood.
Okay, forget about it.
Get to work.
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Yes, sir!
[KAIO PLAYERS counting]
Dude, Sakuma's got a cold?
That doesn't sound
like the guy at all.
Hm?
Come on.
He's the type who'd play
right through appendicitis.
He's got a poster of that runner
who killed himself
for winnin' bronze.
So what would
be important enough
to make him skip practice?
He worships you
like a god, you know.
Kaio Academy doesn't let us
play other school's athletes
without special permission.
But if Sakuma was motivated,
maybe that wouldn't stop him.
It's fine with me if you
want to have your little crush
on that chopper from Katase.
But use your head.
If you go 'round callin'
us losers in public,
the team you've got
might crumble around you.
[KAIO PLAYERS counting]
You understand what I said?
Hey Kazama!
Break time's over!
Oh.
[SANADA]
What's wrong?
Ah, crap.
You are worried about Sakuma.
[KAZAMA]
No.
Sure you're not.
--S'not like he's obsessive--
--Sakuma will lose.
Tsukimoto is just on a different
level than the rest of you.
It won't matter how
hard Sakuma tries.
He'll lose.
Hey, you can smell
the sweet olives blooming.
[KAIO PLAYER 5E]
Uh, sirs?
It's time!
[SANADA]
Yeah, yeah.
We're comin'.
We need to do something
about Sakuma's spot.
[SANADA]
Say what?
Finding a stronger
player to take his place
will be a major
challenge for us.
How can you
even talk like that?
How would Sakuma
feel if he heard you
casually planning his
future with the team
like it means nothing to you?
He's been with us
through thick and thin
and he deserves
some freaking loyalty!
We're loyal to the club.
Showing compassion
and playing favorites
will do nothing to
restore Kaio's reputation.
If a player can't
win internationally,
he shouldn't compete in high
school tournaments, either.
You can't cling to old
ideas during a crisis.
Winter is coming soon.
You're lookin'
stressed out, Dad.
I'm sure you find that funny.
[YURIE] Is it 'cause
of what Ryu said on TV?
Partly, yeah.
Oh, thanks, dear.
[TAKU] There's a first-year on
my club, bit of a dying breed.
I've got him in one of
our key spots right now.
Is he any good?
Let's just say
if an art gallery
were doing an
"awkwardness" exhibit,
this kid'd be on a pedestal.
I didn't scout him at all.
In fact I was against
him being on the team
for the longest time.
I kept turning him away.
Told him it would
only end in suffering.
But he wouldn't listen.
Said he came to Kaio
to become "just like Kazama."
Eventually I caved, figuring I
could make him a team manager.
But you know what?
Kid surprised me.
If you tell him to
drop and give you twenty,
he'll do
a hundred, a thousand.
But table tennis takes
speed and coordination.
You need a
natural aptitude for it.
Sadly, he can never
be like Ryuichi.
But what can I say?
Your old man's a softy.
I can't help
but root for the kid.
You know?
And it's not just him.
It's this whole squad.
Sure, they're not as strong
as our teams in the glory days,
but I love these guys.
They're a really
good bunch of kids.
I just wish Ryuichi
would realize that.
Don't exactly know
what to tell you, Dad.
It sucks when things
don't go your way.
So after junior college,
you got a plan yet?
Hm...
Still thinking.
[traditional music]
C'mon, First Years!
Lemme hear you!
[KATASE PLAYERS]
Sir!
Oh boy.
[KOIZUMI] Hey, what's
the problem, Mr. Tsukimoto?
While we're still young.
[HOSHINO] What're you doin'
here, Akuma? Lemme guess.
Your astigmatism's
so out of control
you got off
at the wrong station?
This isn't
Kaio Academy, you know.
Been puttin' on
weight there, Peco?
Excuse me!
Where may I find
the coach of this club?
[KOIZUMI]
Right here.
Hello sir!
I'm Sakuma, a First Year
at Kaio Academy!
I have come here today to
challenge Tsukimoto to a match.
If you'll allow it, sir!
You heard him.
Okay Akuma, I'll play you.
But you'll lose.
Look who thinks he's so cool!
[OTA]
There goes practice.
I give up.
[KOIZUMI] I don't mind
you playing a match, son.
But doesn't Kaio Academy have
a rule against its students
playing other teams
without permission?
Yes, sir.
If I lose I will be
immediately expelled.
Y'hear that, Tsukimoto?
They run their team
like a police squad.
What, your squad commander
didn't give you his blessing?
I didn't even tell
dispatch I was coming.
So you're ready to face
the firing squad, huh?
Okey doke.
We don't mind giving
you a bit of time.
Just don't blame us when
they're loading the guns.
I want this match
over in fifteen minutes.
We still need to finish
today's training regimen.
You got it, Coach.
Give me your worst.
[SAKUMA] It's been two
years and four months
since we last
had a game, Smile.
[TSUKIMOTO]
You don't say.
[KATASE PLAYER 1H]
Time!
And I'm currently ahead
ninety-six
games to thirty-seven!
[TSUKIMOTO]
I forget the silly details.
Ready!
Don't get cocky just because
Kazama's got it in his head
you're some kinda wonder boy.
Your fancy winning streak
is from playing with amateurs
who can't do much
of anything besides block.
You been splashin'
around the kiddie pool.
Heads up.
[KATASE PLAYER 1H]
One-Love!
[SAKUMA]
What do you know, Smile?
It's almost like
you've gotten better.
[KATASE PLAYER 5A]
This guy's got some skills.
He actually made
Smile return a couple.
Well that's Kaio Academy for ya.
[KATASE PLAYER 1H]
Love-two!
Love-three!
[KATASE PLAYER 1H]
That's four-love!
Eleven-love!
Game to Tsukimoto!
Damn you. Damn you!
Come on, don't fall for
a simple spin shot like that!
Moron!
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
Hey! Stop it, Akuma!
Don't hit Smile, he's my friend!
He's dumb, Peco!
I can't teach him,
he just keeps sucking!
He never gets any better!
[SAKUMA]
Bring it!
[KATASE PLAYER 1H]
That's out!
Two-Eleven!
Game to Tsukimoto!
[SAKUMA]
Son of a bitch.
I can't read his moves at all.
I can't knock him off balance.
He's not even fazed
by my knuckleball.
[KATASE PLAYER 1H]
Tsukimoto leads.
Two games to zero.
[SAKUMA] It's like I'm
playing a college student.
Or a full-on pro.
Where the hell
did I go wrong?
[growls frustratedly]
How is he tripping me up?
You've got a severe
astigmatism, Manabu.
[SAKUMA]
Where did I go wrong?
When your eyes get tired,
stare off into
the distance, okay?
[SAKUMA]
Why am I failing?
I'm hoping you got
your mom's eyes,
instead of bad ones like mine.
Look over there, Manabu.
What do you see?
[SAKUMA'S FATHER]
No, Manabu, look again.
That's a choo-choo,
not a beep-beep.
[SAKUMA]
Where did I go wrong?
In fact, after I
dominate high school
I'm gonna go play in Europe.
Coach says you're gonna
lead off for us, Sakuma.
You should be proud.
[SAKUMA]
How is this happening?
Come on, Manabu.
What do you see?
[KATASE PLAYER 1H]
Five-Love!
Damn it!
Why do you get
to be the one, Smile?
It's not freakin' fair!
I've worked way
too hard for this!
I've worked a hundred times.
No, a thousand times
harder than you ever will!
All so Kazama
would acknowledge me!
And I could put
Peco in his place!
I've given everything
to this game!
Practicing and thinkin'
about it every day and night!
I've read every book,
studied every technique!
So why?
'Cause you don't
have a natural talent
for table tennis, Akuma.
[TSUKIMOTO]
That's all it is.
Just fact.
It's not something
worth screaming about.
That's a load o' crap.
I refuse to believe it.
If you're not gonna
finish our match, Akuma,
go home.
I'm too busy to
watch a meltdown.
[SAKUMA]
It can't be true.
It can't!
[STREET GUY 5A] So there's
all these different theories
about Bruce Lee's death, right?
Hey! Why don't you look
where you're going, ya jerk!
Screw you!
You gonna give me a trophy
for looking where I'm going,
is that it? Huh?
[SAKUMA]
Go on!
Tell me again, big shot!
Tell me where to freaking look!
Sorry pal,
this is goodbye.
Rest in peace now, okay?