[TAKU]
You're going now?
But I could see you
off after Qualifiers.
[YURIE] No way, Dad,
you'll just cry if you do.
Besides, after the
tournament I know you'll want
to jump back into
practice mode.
You know,
your mom will miss you.
When are you coming back home?
When my dreams come true.
You should visit me!
Flying overseas is not for me.
Where'd you get the money?
[YURIE]
Sold my car!
[TAKU]
I'll be damned.
Have you told Ryuichi?
Are you gonna?
[YURIE]
Mm...
No.
But Ryu will be fine.
No one's waited for a
hero longer than he has,
and all that waiting is
bound to pay off eventually.
In fact, I'm sure of it.
Someday, somebody
will come and save him.
[YURIE]
When he wins,
tell him he has to call
Aunt Emiko, all right?
[HOSHINO (CHILD)] I've traveled
far from Planet Ping Pong
to protect Earth's peace!
I am the unbeatable hero!
The bringer of justice!
Yes! It is I!
The totally invincible
ping pong player!
My name is--!
Can you still
play on that knee?
[KAZAMA]
That's your paddle?
I ran up to
Don-Quijote to buy it
so I could have some
real fun with you, Dragon!
[MALE SPECTATOR 10A]
A twiddle penhold blade?
Never seen anyone use one!
[MALE SPECTATOR 10B] He's
gonna flip it during play?
The inverted rubber
should strengthen his returns
when he gets pushed back.
But we can't forget Peco's gift,
which is his speed attack
close to the table.
So I put one of his
springy, pips-out rubbers
back on one side.
And gave him a blade with
a twiddle penhold grip
to make twiddling easy.
Now he can choose pips-out for
speed, or inverted for spin,
and switch on the fly, for both
forehand and backhand strokes!
Constantly changing sides
will drive his opponent nuts
trying to guess what's
gonna come at him next.
Not an easy play style, but
Peco picked it up in no time!
[KAZAMA]
This is a toy.
You won't stand a chance
against me with this thing.
[HOSHINO] You're right
about my knee, you know.
It is messed up pretty bad.
But as an athlete,
you're really high up there.
So I think I'll
take advantage of that.
I'm just gonna
climb on your back,
take a big ol' leap...
...and fly.
Sounds to me like you need
a strong dose of reality.
The way you're
talking is delusional.
We humans aren't built to fly.
Ha!
Great, now he thinks
I'm sick in the head!
[crowd cheering]
[KAZAMA]
No, humans can't fly.
But if we could...
If we could...!
[HOSHINO] Hot damn,
this guy is intimidating.
Guess that's a world
champ for you, though.
No.
Don't let him get to you,
or you're done for.
Flinch and you'll lose.
Fear him and you'll die!
All right.
Here goes!
[KOIZUMI]
A hero, huh?
[HOSHINO]
'Kay.
Seriously?
[KAZAMA]
Yeah!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Love-one!
[in Chinese] He brute-forced
that backhand return.
[KONG, in Chinese] He doesn't
want to admit Hoshino's talent.
I know how he feels.
Aw, damn.
Good start.
Love-two!
That was vicious.
Dragon went all the way from
there to the opposite corner.
He's messing with his head.
[KAZAMA]
Yes!
Yeah!
Crap!
[KOIZUMI]
Got a moment?
Yeah, for what?
[KOIZUMI] Hoshino is playing
his big match right now.
Aren't you going
to cheer him on?
Do you believe in
heroes, Coach Koizumi?
[KOIZUMI]
Heroes?
Who swoop in to save you
when you're in a pinch.
The kind you can count on
no matter how ugly it gets.
'Cause you know
they'll be victorious.
[KOIZUMI]
Huh.
Can't say I've ever
really thought about it.
Why?
Do you believe in heroes?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Yes.
He went away, and I've
waited a long time for him.
And today,
he's finally coming back.
[KOIZUMI]
Yeah?
"He" who?
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
The hero appears!
You're one cool
customer, Dragon.
I like that about you.
The thing is, you can
only climb so high
lookin' down on people before
you gotta spread your wings.
[TSUKIMOTO]
He's coming back strong.
[HOSHINO]
I'm the hero.
You got that?
[HOSHINO]
My name is--!
Yutaka Hoshino!
And don't you forget it!
[KAZAMA]
You'll find out one day.
The sorrow of invincibility.
The great pain of praise.
The weight of what you carry.
The isolation, and the anguish.
Eventually your efforts
will feel meaningless,
your victories hollow.
[KAIO PRESIDENT] But you can
never let those doubts stop you,
understand?
[MICHIO]
This isn't good, Peco.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Doubt makes you vulnerable.
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Nine-love!
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Vulnerability brings defeat.
And defeat is death.
[MICHIO]
Don't let Kazama set the pace!
[KAZAMA]
Ignore the emptiness!
Thirst for victory
with all you've got!
[MICHIO]
Your backhand, Peco!
Use your backhand!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Ten-love!
[MICHIO]
Come on!
Yeah!
[KAZAMA]
Thirst!
With all you are!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Eleven-love!
Game to Kazama!
You are done!
Your training is pathetic!
Thinkin' you could win
with some trick you learned
at the last minute?
Disgusting!
Holy crap-sticks.
You don't mess around, Dragon.
It's friggin' sweet.
Love ya, kid.
[KAZAMA]
Drive.
Short pips backhand.
He sees 'em coming.
Peco's switches
are too by-the-book.
You know better'n that, Peco.
Yes!
[KAZAMA] There is no
shortcut to victory.
You have to climb
that steep mountain
one finger-hold at a time.
Below you,
the never-ending abyss.
Pressing on is your only choice!
[KAZAMA (CHILD)]
Dad!
[NORIO]
Birds have it good.
They can get high
above this mountain
and they barely have to try.
Figure they've been watching
our ugly wars and struggles
long before there
were airplanes,
thinking how stupid we are.
I wish I were a bird.
[KAZAMA (CHILD)]
Careful, Dad.
That's dangerous!
Dad!
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Never let them see you cry.
From now on, defeat is death.
Might as well
cut off your own arm
if you're gonna
settle for compromises.
In triumph, we find truth.
Win, Ryuichi!
For your family,
for Kaio, for Poseidon.
Win!
[YOUNG BOY 10A]
I want Carpaccio!
[MOTHER 10A] Yes, that
does look good, doesn't it?
[KAZAMA (CHILD)]
No, udon!
I wanna eat udon!
[MOTHER 10B] But Ryu, I
don't think the rest of us--
[KAZAMA (CHILD)]
Udon! Udon!
We have to have udon!
[MOTHER 10C]
Well that's that.
Once Ryu's made up his mind,
there's no reasoning with him.
[MOTHER 10A] All right,
let's go find udon.
[YOUNG BOY 10A]
What?
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
He just wasn't popular.
There aren't
enough wreaths here.
Ryuichi, go order five more!
And Emiko, of all
times to be sick!
If your husband wasn't
doing such crap business,
you wouldn't get all
these strange diseases!
[EMIKO] All families have
their own sets of rules,
so please, just
try to bear with it.
[KAIO PRESIDENT] Don't start
thinking someone will save you,
because nobody will!
If you don't want to be
bullied, get stronger.
Win, win, and win some more!
[KAZAMA]
What's wrong, "hero?"
You're still losing!
Heroes are winners!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
That's enough, Kazama.
Calm down.
Aren't you gonna fly now?
Aren't you gonna save everyone?
[SANADA]
Damn, Kazama's driven.
He never gets like this, even
in the championship finals.
[NEKOTA]
Yeah, right?
His majesty is angry.
Looks like Peco's
adorable personality
has woken the dragon.
Ryuichi thinks
being a champion's
the lot he was given in life.
Like he didn't have a choice.
I don't think he's enjoyed
table tennis in a long time.
For years, it's been
nothing but pain for him,
and he's just carried on.
That's one brand of strength,
but it's a damn shame.
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Eleven-one!
Game to Kazama!
[crowd cheering]
Okey-doke, see you
guys when the dust settles.
Hoshino.
[HOSHINO]
Huh?
I'm not saying I like
you, but good luck.
Waste him.
[HOSHINO]
Will do.
[KOIZUMI]
Look how he's moving.
It's completely locked up.
He and his knee aren't
exactly friends right now.
[humming]
[KAZAMA]
Is your knee getting worse?
[HOSHINO]
Aw, you're so sweet, Kaz.
Y'feel sorry for me?
Gonna let me win the next game?
Hardly.
So then why bother asking?
[HOSHINO]
Long serve?
Short?
Don't think, kid, you
don't have the brains for it.
[HOSHINO]
Long!
Hit to the middle, then.
But he returns
great from there!
Doesn't this guy
have any weaknesses?
If he keeps me running,
he'll wear me out!
You know better, Peco.
[HOSHINO]
I can't pace myself.
[TAMURA]
That is not your game.
[KAZAMA]
Yes!
[HOSHINO]
He's so good.
It's turning into a replay
of our first game.
He's pushin' me away from the
table so I can't make fast hits.
How do I counter that?
Dammit.
[humming]
[HOSHINO]
Hey. What's that weird song?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Is he a tough opponent?
[HOSHINO] He's freaking
ping pong incarnate!
[TSUKIMOTO] You need to
find the fun in it, Peco.
Time flies when
you're having fun.
Play like you used to, when
you had such a great time
you forgot everything else.
Anything that bothered you.
Even a busted knee.
You're gonna be fine.
Like you always said.
The strongest players
let you fly the highest.
Right?
[HOSHINO]
Yeah.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Can you fly?
[HOSHINO]
Yeah!
[HOSHINO (CHILD)] What's
that you're humming?
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
Is it weird?
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
Yeah, a little bit.
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
Just somethin' I made up.
It's called the Hero Song.
[humming continues]
[HOSHINO laughing maniacally]
[in Chinese]
That's scary.
What's with him?
[in Chinese]
Don't ask me.
[HOSHINO]
Hey Dragon!
Get ready 'cause
I'm taking you to school!
[HOSHINO] And here's your
big lesson for the day!
Ping pong is a freaking blast!
You see, I can fly!
And blaze like the sun!
And flash like lightning!
All at once!
My neurons are firing!
I'm all lit up
to blow you away!
Reaction!
Reflex!
I'm faster than sound!
Faster than light!
[TAMURA]
That's more like it.
Love ya, kid.
[HOSHINO] I'm a
superhuman hyperdrive!
Blink and I'm gone!
[TAKU]
Hey! Backhand!
[crowd cheering]
[KOIZUMI]
Now I'm startin' to see.
Hello, hero.
[HOSHINO]
Look at me, Smile!
Look how fast I can move!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Eleven-six.
Game to Hoshino!
[crowd cheering]
[KAZAMA]
Pips-in drive.
Pips-out backhand?
That's it.
[KAZAMA]
Pips-out again?
Good!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Five all!
Yeah! Woo!
You see that?
This is what I call a match!
I can attack with either
rubber; it's awesome!
[crowd cheering]
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
This is a surprise.
[in Chinese]
He's got good instincts.
This must sting for Kazama.
[in Chinese]
Maybe not.
Hoshino's style is offbeat.
It's like he loves the sport
so much he can't hold it in.
Getting to play with
someone like that--
For me, at least, it's...
[HOSHINO]
Got him!
Tricky bastard.
When the hell'd he learn
how to chop like that?
Well, it worked.
He's got Kazama in panic mode.
[KAZAMA]
There are no heroes!
You can only rely
on your own strength!
[SAKUMA]
Their reactions are sick!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Eleven-eight!
Game to Hoshino!
[HOSHINO]
Yeah!
[crowd chering]
[in Chinese]
They're neck and neck now.
Yeah.
[SANADA]
Come on, Kazama!
By the way, don't
worry about my knee.
'Cause we're making this match
one for the record books.
Still love ya though, Dragon.
Mm-wa!
Don't push your luck.
[KAZAMA]
Yes!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Out!
--[KAZAMA] Yeah!
--[TAKU] There you go!
[MALE UMPIRE 10A]
Five-six Kazama!
[in Chinese]
This is a good game.
[NORIO]
Here comes, Ryuichi!
That's great!
You're good at this, little guy!
Havin' fun?
You like playing this, buddy?
[SANADA]
Don't step back, Kazama!
[KAZAMA]
Shut up!
[SANADA]
I think he actually smiled.
[NEKOTA]
At what?
It's about time.
[KAZAMA] All of my cells
are singing out with joy.
"Faster," they command me.
"Faster! Faster!"
My concentration is a
force, shutting out the world.
As I speed up, reality
around me slows to a crawl.
Yet he keeps learning and
growing, like a sponge.
I explode into motion.
But I'm steadily
being outpaced.
I feel myself being left behind.
It's becoming obvious
who the better player is.
And yet, I don't feel anxious.
I'm striking with all I've got.
Reacting with all I am.
There's no time to be afraid.
Problem?
Not at all.
Truth is,
I feel really good.
Yeah.
Me, too.
So uh, this is match
point for me, Dragon.
[KAZAMA]
Yep.
This is as far as I go, hero.
[HOSHINO]
Seriously?
[KAZAMA] My wings
can't take any more.
Will you bring me
to this place again?
I get it now.
[KAZAMA] All of my cells
are singing out with joy.
"Faster," they command me.
"Faster! Faster!"
Reality around
me slows to a crawl.
Yet he keeps
learning and growing.
I'm being outpaced,
but I don't feel anxious.
There's no time to be afraid.
There's no need to be afraid!
I like this place.
It's glorious.
[HOSHINO]
You were so cool, Dragon.
[KAZAMA]
And you were right.
People can fly.
We can fly.