This is terrible.
I wish I'd never been born.
Can't believe I got skunked.
The whole world's laughing
at me right now, I know it!
[HOSHINO groans]
[TAMURA] Do me a favor,
Peco, and go home.
It's hard to work
over your pouting.
Damn you, China. What's your
weakness? You're too good.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Hook loop! Inside out loop!
Smash! Back! Inside out!
Fore!
Crazy, his coach makes him
change his stroke on the fly
and he's still
hitting every target!
And Kong won't even play
a single game with us.
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 2C]
Course not. He thinks we suck!
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 2A] Dude.
You think that's the rubber
you can only get in China?
[TSUJIDO PLAYER 2C] Nah,
he probably stopped getting it
since he's off the
Provincial team.
[in Chinese] Shut up!
You're distracting me!
Uh, sorry, boys...
Would you mind being
a little quieter so
Kong can concentrate?
Yeah. Of course,
sorry, sir.
[in Chinese]
What's wrong, Wenge?
[KONG, in Chinese]
Is the chopper with glasses
out today, too?
Kong wants to know if the kid
with glasses is here today.
The one with the chop?
Yes, sir. We can get him.
Hey, Goda!
Kong wants to play you!
[KONG, in Chinese]
Let's keep going, Coach.
Where is he?
[TSUKIMOTO] It's safe
and quiet in here.
I don't mind it.
I'm comfortable.
If I don't make a sound, I'll
be fine. I can stay in here.
I'll be so quiet they won't even
hear me breathe. Like a robot.
No! Leave me alone!
I told you. You can
go get him yourself.
When Peco's not here,
he's usually at the dojo
by the rail station. I already
said I'd draw you a map
if you think
you'll get lost.
Look, we're nice guys,
we don't like hazing.
But you're forcing
our hand here, bro!
That's completely
illogical.
[OTA] Don't use
math words with me!
Yeah, that's against team rules!
No algebra talk during practice!
[KOIZUMI]
That's enough.
Look, Mr. Tsukimoto. I'd rather
you not go to Tamura's.
Or play Hoshino anymore.
Why wouldn't I
play him? He's good.
Yeah. I'm confused.
Because you
go easy on him.
And that's bad
for your training.
I don't do that.
It's subconscious, I guess.
Mr. Tsukimoto, I want
you training with me
every day before school
from now on, five A.M.
You lack a thirst to win,
and we have to fix that
before Championships,
because if there's anything
a true competitor needs,
it's fighting spirit!
Of course, it's not mandatory.
But I'm sure you want
to reach your potential.
So I look forward to seeing
you tomorrow, bright and early.
[TSUKIMOTO] I'm not
practicing early.
Certainly not at five.
[KOIZUMI] No problem,
take your time.
I'll be here when you're ready.
He'll wait for you. Sounds
like a great love story.
Coach and Smile,
sittin' in a tree!
Carbonation has gotten totally
weak these days. I know it's
part of that all-natural-
organic-health-craze crap,
but can't a guy have some
freakin' bubbles in his soda?
Hey, Smile, what's up?
I guess practice is over?
Yeah.
And lemme guess,
because I skipped,
the jerks made
you all run laps.
Yeah.
[HOSHINO]
That sucks.
Those upperclassmen
shouldn't harass you guys.
I'm the one not showin' up.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Mm.
Well, that'll end
soon enough.
I've decided I'm
gonna quit the team.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Mm.
Seriously, that's
your response?
If you don't like it,
then quit.
Don't force yourself
to play a game.
[HOSHINO] Exactly my point!
It's supposed to be fun, right?
[HOSHINO] So, uh, how long
till Championship Qualifiers?
Two months.
Aw, that quick? Not even time
to feel sorry for myself.
Old Lady, we're
taking table four.
[TAMURA]
I'm charging you for it.
[KOIZUMI] Four mornings
in a row, Mr. Tsukimoto.
I find that five A.M.'s a
bit too quiet in the gym
for just one old man
making serves at the wall.
Why don't you come train,
like I asked?
Why should I be the only
one with extra practice?
I'd rather just sleep.
Didja know you're deprivin' my
life of meaning? A coach's job
has no purpose without
a great athlete to train.
Don'tcha want to be the protégé
who defines my twilight years?
Not really.
Well... Startin' today,
I don't wantcha thinking
about anything other
than table tennis.
What are you thinking
about right now?
Question five.
That's nonsense! What good
has high school English class
ever done for anybody?
Quiet, Mr. Koizumi!
We can't focus!
[KOIZUMI]
Sorry, kids, sorry.
[TSUKIMOTO] It's all
just killing time.
[HOSHINO snores]
[KOIZUMI]
Hm?
Playing ping pong
or learning vocab.
Both just kill time
until we die.
[HOSHINO]
What do you say, Smile?
You a peanut man
or a caramel man?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Uh, caramel?
Yeah, right? It's just
basic common sense!
But the convenience store
by my place only stocks
the peanut ones--it's lame!
It's like a torture experiment!
Who wants peanuts?
Mr. Tsukimoto.
What are you eating?
It's a hammager, sir.
Diction, boy, diction.
Hamburger.
Hamburger?
[KOIZUMI] It's a
lump of cholesterol.
I don't want you
eating that. Here.
[HOSHINO]
Who-o-oa!
[KOIZUMI] Starting today,
I'll be making your lunches
with food that's
actually good for you.
I call it the "Strong For
Ping Pong Diet." Enjoy!
You can't make
me eat this.
True love!
[KOIZUMI]
Yes! Love!
[KOIZUMI hums]
You seem happy, Jo.
Let's just say that springtime
has come again
for this old fool.
Hm? What's that?
A love letter from Coach?
[HOSHINO]
Oh, ouch. Tough love.
Throw it away.
Mix up your attacks!
Stay on it, more follow through!
And keep those feet moving!
Does Coach always get like this
when qualifiers
are coming around?
No, I've never
seen him this way.
It is spring;
maybe he's in heat.
Your moves are too repetitive;
you need to vary your game!
The tough guy act's not gonna
work with Smile, though,
he hates getting yelled at.
Don't let him ace you--
knock 'im back!
Why aren't you attacking?
Make him miss!
See, that was
the time to strike!
Do what I told you!
Are you even trying?
Where are you going?
The game's not over yet. Wait!
He's out.
[KOIZUMI] Mr. Tsukimoto!
Come back!
Yup, and I guess
that's my cue.
[KOIZUMI grunts]
[HOSHINO] Dude! Check out
the view of Mount Fuji today!
You can't be in a bad mood!
The weather's too awesome!
[TSUKIMOTO] Everything
makes me so tired lately.
I hate dealing with people.
And even ping pong is getting
more complicated now.
It's not like
when we were kids.
[HOSHINO] He's a little
too hard on you, yeah,
but I think he's
a smart coach.
He's giving you the
training you need.
You're wrong about that.
I'm only in it to pass the time.
Having fun is enough for me.
I don't want to
sacrifice things I like
or drag other people
down just to win.
[OTA]
Just bailed, man.
Hey!
[KAZAMA] Gentlemen!
My name is Ryuichi Kazama,
second-year at Kaio
Academy. I've come here
to observe your practice
today, if you will allow it!
Kaio, huh?
[KATASE PLAYER 1A]
That's Dragon!
He was the high school
champ last year, right?
[KATASE PLAYER 1B]
Fourth at World Juniors, too.
[KATASE PLAYER 1C]
What's he doing at our school?
[KATASE PLAYER 1B]
Headhunting?
[KATASE PLAYER 1A] Yeah,
probably came to watch me.
[KATASE PLAYER 1B]
Dude, shut up.
[KATASE PLAYER 1A]
Guy looks military.
Is he really in high school?
Would you mind stepping
outside with me, Mr. Kazama?
I think you're making my
boys feel a touch nervous.
[KOIZUMI]
Mr. Tsukimoto isn't here today.
He's the one you're
interested in, am I right?
[KAZAMA] I first saw him play
in a middle school tournament.
He lost, but his skills
were impressive.
Control, speed, playmaking,
reflexes, concentration.
He was far above
middle school level.
Honestly, he was good enough to
make me question my own skills.
And yet you said he lost.
Who beat him?
[KAZAMA] A guy
named Manabu Sakuma.
He's a freshman at Kaio
this year, but I'm told
he trained at the same dojo
as Tsukimoto for a while.
[KOIZUMI]
I see.
[KAZAMA] Human reaction speed
maxes out at point-one second.
Becoming elite at table tennis
means getting as close to
that threshold as possible.
[KOIZUMI] Those are the words
of your school's president.
[KAZAMA] Yes. Our approach
is fundamentally different
from a casual
ping pong club.
That was a dig against
my school, wasn't it?
You're implying
we're a bad fit
for a player with
Mr. Tsukimoto's talents.
[KAZAMA] As I see it, he's a
swan among ducklings here.
[KOIZUMI]
Question for you, Mr. Kazama.
Whaddya suppose are the odds
that my "first year swan"
will beat you at qualifiers
two months from now?
Do you think he can?
[KAZAMA]
Not a chance.
I wanna be the
number-one player
on the whole freakin'
Earth. The best!
I want that gold World
Champion trophy on my shelf.
It's my biggest dream.
Guess we're different
that way, aren't we?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Mm.
It's all right; it makes
things simpler for me.
I hate losing, so I don't
care about hurting
other people's feelings
when I play 'em.
That's their problem--
I just want to win.
[TSUKIMOTO] Yeah, fair enough.
I'll be rooting for you.
Then promise me you'll come
to the club tomorrow, okay?
Cause practice is totally
pointless when you're not there.
[GIRL squeals]
[HOSHINO] It's shaping up
to be another hot summer!
Ya never answered me, Coach.
Why am I the only one
training this way?
Because you're a different sort
of player; it's simple as that.
Let's get goin', sweetheart.
No time to waste.
Two tables, damn.
The old man's brutal.
[KOIZUMI] Too slow,
too slow, too slow!
Pick up the pace!
No stopping!
Move, move!
And those ain't easy
serves to return, either.
I'm surprised Smile
is keeping up with 'em.
He runs a crazy fast
marathon, you know.
We're in the middle of
practice, Hoshino--
where'd you get that candy from?
Crossover!
Go! Faster!
The corner store.
[KOIZUMI]
Move!
No napping, Tsukimoto!
Do you see a couch?
What's the point
of all this, sir?
To get stronger.
But that's stupid.
It's how you win.
I'm not interested in shiny
medals. That's not why I play.
Some views you can't appreciate
until you're at the top.
I'm telling you
I don't care.
I think you give up and
withdraw into your shell
whenever you're challenged.
I live my life how I want.
It's none of your business.
All right, Mr. Tsukimoto, fine.
I challenge you to a match.
If you win, I promise to never
interfere with you again.
You'll be as free as a bird.
[TSUKIMOTO]
And if I lose?
[KOIZUMI] "Woof! Woof!"
You'll be my dog on a leash.
You'll obey my every command.
This is a best-of-three match!
Service to Coach Koizumi!
I'll make you heel.
Ready!
What the crap? Does the old
man really think he can win?
Not a chance. He was
famous back in his time,
but he's no match
for Tsukimoto now.
[KOIZUMI] It's time you got some
perspective, Mr. Tsukimoto.
I'll show you how soft and
weak your game actually is.
[TSUKIMOTO gasps]
[TSUKIMOTO]
Wha--?!
Aw, come on!
That wasn't a fair serve!
[KOIZUMI] Sure it was!
You returned it, didn't you?
[OTA] Point counts!
One-Love!
Kinda cheap trick there,
Coach, isn't it?
He's good.
[KOIZUMI] Are you gonna
get mad, Mr. Tsukimoto?
Of course not.
You'll shrink away,
like you always do
when you're confronted...
Here!
[KOIZUMI]
...like a scared child.
Yeah!
Listen to the old guy roar.
He's doing it for effect. He
knows exactly what Smile hates.
[KOIZUMI] I can read
you like a book.
If I send the ball to
you at this angle...
You'll return it
the same every time.
Straight, almost flat.
Leaving you exposed.
Like that!
[TSUKIMOTO sighs]
[KOIZUMI] And you mentally
quit at the drop of a hat.
Accepting defeat so
gracefully. It's naïve!
You'll never cross the sea
on such delicate wings.
Setbacks and defeats!
Loss and grief!
Holy crap.
[KOIZUMI] Isolation and turmoil!
Anguish and despair!
Not the kinda play
you expect from a guy
with one foot in the grave.
[KOIZUMI]
Nihilism and ruin!
[HOSHINO]
He's relentless.
[OTA]
Point! Five-love!
I'm gonna teach you
everything, Mr. Tsukimoto!
That's eight-love!
How fragile you are!
And how to find the
strength to conquer!
[TSUKIMOTO]
It's safe and quiet here.
I don't mind it.
I'm comfortable.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Someone's coming!
No, it's okay. If I don't
make a sound, I'll be fine.
If I go outside...
it'll happen again.
[KOIZUMI
Hah!
[TSUKIMOTO gasps]
[OTA] Eleven-four!
Game to Coach Koizumi!
[KOIZUMI]
Hm.
[TSUKIMOTO]
The hero appears...
I don't believe it.
Coach may actually win.
[HOSHINO chuckles]
[HOSHINO] Once a softy,
always a softy, eh, Smile?
You'll never change.
[KOIZUMI]
Hah!
Your weakest spot
is down the middle.
Where players have to choose
between forehand or backhand.
Without fail, you'll go
with a long backhand chop.
Utterly predictable.
Look out!
I hope for your sake you're
not going easy on me,
or showing me mercy. Because
I'm about to make you my dog!
You'll shake when I say shake!
Spin three times
and bark on command!
I'll make ya do it too,
I promise! Put a leash around
your neck and walk ya through
the neighborhood every day!
What a nice boy,
respecting his elder!
A shining example for
your whole generation!
[TSUKIMOTO] Why can't
everybody leave me alone?
I'm not getting mad,
I'm not laughing at anything.
I'm just here! I don't even
make a noise when I breathe.
I just sit in the back, being
quiet, doing what I'm told.
Like a good little robot.
[TSUKIMOTO]
The hero appears...
Who's that?
[KOIZUMI grunts]
Hand on the table!
That'll cost you a point!
Shut up. You really think
that's something worth
screaming about?
I want you to be
quiet too, Coach.
It's not distracting me.
It just pisses me off.
Hey! Get down! That definitely
seems against the rules!
All right.
Look who got cool.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Yeah!
Eleven-six!
Game to Tsukimoto!
Tsukimoto found his second
wind. Coach is screwed.
Yeah, you may be right, but it's
been one heck of a battle.
[KATASE PLAYER 1I]
Coach is over seventy, right?
This has to be rough on him.
[HOSHINO] I can't
believe it, Smile.
When did you learn
to play like this?
[TAMURA] The kid's
not exactly friendly.
Can't he even say hello?
[YOUNG HOSHINO]
He never smiles.
[YOUNG TSUKIMOTO]
Ping pong?
[YOUNG HOSHINO] Softly, like
you're holding an egg. Okay?
[TSUKIMOTO yells]
[KOIZUMI pants]
[TSUKIMOTO] Stand up so we
can finish our match, sir.
It's really annoying the way
you pause after every point.
[robotic noises accompany
TSUKIMOTO's movements]
Do you see a
couch over there?
[KOIZUMI] I'm dizzy.
I need five minutes.
[TSUKIMOTO] Umpire.
My opponent's withdrawing.
No! I was only kidding!
I take it back!
Very good, Mr. Tsukimoto.
I was just testing you.
Way to stay tough!
I don't think Coach
is lookin' so hot.
Yeah, no, he's
totally broken.
Now Tsukimoto's being cruel.
[KOIZUMI] You're finally
starting to understand,
aren't you? You don't chase
the ball. The ball chases you.
Stand up to it, make it
bend to your will,
and you'll grow strong.
You feel it, right?
You feel it chasing you! Now,
show me what you can really do!
[KOIZUMI] Now the corner.
Prove you can return it!
[KOIZUMI] That's it, boy.
The ball chases you.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Can I be like you?
[YOUNG TSUKIMOTO] Do you think
I'll ever be like you, Peco?
[YOUNG TSUKIMOTO] Cause I wanna
be. I wanna be just like you.
[KATASE PLAYER 2C]
Aw, man! Coach is down!
[OTA] Guys, I think I
heard something crack.
[KATASE PLAYER 2D]
Is he dead?
First-years, take him
to the nurse! Hurry!
But look, he's smiling,
maybe he's okay.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe that just
means brain damage.
I'm heading out now,
Peco. See ya.
[HOSHINO]
Huh?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Later.
You can't leave!
It's your fault he fell!
I haven't dismissed
you from practice!
You don't get to ignore me!
Hey! Get back here, Tsukimoto!