OOFF!
(CHUCKLING)
[LONDARK]
IT HAS BEEN FAR TOO LONG.
[NYANTA]
LONDARK!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE
WITH PLANT HWYADEN...?
TELL ME, LONDARK!
AW NOW THAT'S NO WAY
TO GREET AN OLD FRIEND.
BESIDES, WHAT REASON DO WE HAVE
TO FIGHT WITH ONE ANOTHER?
THEN AGAIN I CAN'T HAVE YOU
IN MY WAY EITHER. NOW CAN I?
[NYANTA] DO YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU ARE DOING?
HOW THIS IS GOING TO WORK?!
[LONDARK] YES, YES. OF
COURSE I DO! I DO THE JOB.
THEY GIVE ME MONEY.
IT'S QUITE SIMPLE, REALLY.
I'M HERE TO PROVIDE SECURITY FOR
THE GENERAL'S LITTLE TOY TRAIN!
[NYANTA] I WAS TALKING
ABOUT THE CONSEQUENCES!
[LONDARK] "CONSEQUENCES"?
SORRY, MY FRIEND...
I'M AFRAID THAT WASN'T
INCLUDED IN THE MANUAL.
[LONDARK]
INFERNO STRIKE! HWAH!
COME TO THINK OF IT...!
THAT SEEMS TO BE A THEME
FOR THIS PLACE DOESN'T IT?
I NEVER GOT THE MANUAL
FOR THIS WORLD EITHER!
ARE YOU SAYING...
WE MIGHT END UP FIGHTING A WAR
WITH THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND,
SHIROE?
[SHIROE] IF WE'RE THE
LEAST BIT RESPONSIBLE,
THEN WE HAVE TO
CONSIDER IT, YES.
[NYANTA, THINKING] TO PUT IT
SUCCINCTLY, THIS WORLD WE'RE IN
IS RIGHT ON THE EDGE OF
GOING TO WAR ANY MINUTE.
SHIROE‐ECCHI DID WHAT
HE COULD TO MAKE
THAT POINT CLEAR AT THE
ROUND TABLE'S FIRST CONFERENCE.
HE WASN'T JOKING, EITHER. WE
HAVE TO FIND OUT FOR OURSELVES
HOW WE'RE GOING TO DEAL
WITH THAT THREAT AND
KEEP IT AT BAY IF WE CAN.
LISTEN TO ME, VERY
CAREFULLY, LONDARK...
ALL YOU'RE DOING IS
HELP CREATE A WAR!
THERE'S NO NEED TO
BE SO DRAMATIC.
IF YOU FEEL THE NEED TO COMPLAIN
TO SOMEONE ABOUT GOING TO WAR,
TAKE IT UP WITH THE PERSON
OF THE LAND WHO HIRED ME!
[NYANTA] GUILT BY ASSOCIATION
IS STILL GUILT, LONDARK!
[LONDARK] EH. NOT FROM
WHERE I STAND! UWAH!
IT'S NOT MY WAR!
THINK OF THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
WHO'LL DIE BECAUSE OF THIS!
YOU MISS WHO I SAID HIRED ME?!
THEY'RE THE ONES
WHO WANT THIS WAR!
[LONDARK]
FROST‐
GWAH!
UWAH!
YAHHHHH!
(STRUGGLING)
WE CAN PREVENT IT
FROM HAPPENING!
DON'T YOU GET IT?!
NEVER HEAR OF A QUEST
FOR PEACE BEFORE!
NOW BACK OFF!
REALLY? DO YOU SERIOUSLY
STILL CONSIDER THIS A GAME?
DO NOT CONDESCEND ME!
I NEVER WANTED THIS...!
THIS PLACE...
THIS PLACE BROUGHT ME HERE,
IT WAS NOT MY CHOICE!
[LONDARK] I NEVER
GOT AN INVITATION.
I NEVER GOT MY
CHANCE TO RSVP.
OH?
[LONDARK]
I WAS ABDUCTED!
WHAT AM I THE ONLY ONE?
DID YOU GET A DIALOGUE
BOX LETTING YOU DECIDE?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO BE
KIDNAPPED? "YES" OR "NO"?
[LONDARK] I DIDN'T
ASK TO BE HERE
AND I DON'T LIKE BEING HERE.
DO YOU AND YOUR LITTLE LOG
HORIZON FRIENDS ENJOY THIS?
DO YOU ACTUALLY
PREFER BEING HERE?!
SHUT UP...! YOU KNOW DAMN GOOD
AND WELL
NONE OF US WERE INVITED TO
MAKE THIS PLACE OUR HOME!
THEN DON'T STAND THERE AND
LECTURE ME ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE'S
WARS WHEN THEY'RE OUT THERE
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF US!
[LONDARK] THEY TAKE SOMETHING
FROM ME, I TAKE FROM THEM.
IT'S AN EVEN TRADE.
THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH THAT...
HMPH.
AND YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE!
HWAH! HWAH! HWAH!
(EXPLOSION)
UWAAHHH!
(GROAN)
[LONDARK] DON'T HOLD
BACK ON ME, SWASHBUCKLER!
OR IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
[NYANTA, THINKING] I HATE TO SAY
IT,
BUT LONDARK HAS A POINT, MYAH.
WE DIDN'T ASK TO BE HERE.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE A KIDNAPPING.
WE'RE VICTIMS AND OUTSIDERS...
IT WAS UNFAIR. AND I SUPPOSE
IT'S ONLY RIGHT
THAT SOME OF US WOULD RESENT IT,
AND LASH OUT IN ANGER, AND
WANT TO SEE IT TORN DOWN.
I COULD USE MY FIGHTING ABILITY
TO REMOVE LONDARK
AND ANYONE ELSE FOR THAT MATTER,
BUT IT'S ONLY A TEMPORARY
SOLUTION AT BEST, MPH.
(NYANTA EXHALES)
[NYANTA, THINKING]
BUT REALLY...
IT WOULDN'T ACCOMPLISH
ANYTHING...
AND WE'D BE RIGHT BACK
WHERE WE STARTED, MYAH.
[NYANTA] HUH?
[LONDARK] TURBULENCE!
HWAH!
(GROANING)
[LONDARK] SO...!
YOU HAVE A BETTER WAY
TO HANDLE THIS, OLD FRIEND?
SHOULD I JUST LAY BACK
AND LET THIS WORLD
HAVE ITS WAY WITH ME?
I'M SORRY I CAN'T DO THAT!
(STRUGGLING)
(GRUNT) MPH.
[NYANTA] LONDARK... WHAT YOU'VE
SAID IS TRUE OF ALL MANKIND.
IT'S NOTHING BUT A
CHILD'S CONUNDRUM!
WE'RE ALL BORN THE SAME.
PEOPLE, EVERY ONE OF US,
DON'T HAVE A SAY IN OUR BIRTH.
IT'S UNFAIR, ISN'T IT...?
BUT WE ALL END UP HAVING
TO DEAL WITH IT, RIGHT?
[LONDARK] THAT'S DIFFERENT.
UWAH!
(STRUGGLING)
(SCREAMING)
[NYANTA, STRAINING]
WE ALL WOKE UP IN THIS WORLD!
NONE OF US HAD
A SAY IN IT!
NONE OF USE HAD A
CHOICE! WE'RE JUST HERE!
YOU'RE NOT THE
ONLY ONE, LONDARK!
WHETHER YOU'RE IN THIS GAME,
BACK FROM WHERE WE CAME FROM,
OR ANY OTHER WORLD
FOR THAT MATTER.
YES, I'VE HEARD ALL
THAT DRIVEL BEFORE...
YOU CAN WAG YOUR FINGER
AT ME ALL YOU WANT,
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S A
SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR
WHO CAN KICK ME OUT AND
KEEP ME FROM COMING BACK.
[LONDARK] AND OH YEAH, I'M
NOT EVEN ALLOWED TO DIE.
[LONDARK] BUT IF YOU KNOW
HOW, THEN BY ALL MEANS DO IT!
[LONDARK] KILL ME! PUT ME
OUT OF MY MISERY, URGHA...!
(STAFF CLATTERING)
UWAH... AH. UGH...
(SWORD SLIDING OUT)
[MIZPHA] BE CAREFUL WHAT YOU
WISH FOR, LONDARK...
YOU MIGHT GET IT.
[LONDARK] U‐UGH...
(STRUGGLING)
(GIGGLE)
(SCREAMING)
[NYANTA]
UH!
YOU "ADVENTURERS" ARE SO
MARVELOUS!
YOU CAN KILL AND DIE TO YOUR
HEART'S CONTENT
ANY TIME YOU WISH!
[NYANTA] UH... WHAT WAS THAT...?
[MIZPHA] HUH?
[NYANTA]
WHAT DID YOU KILL HIM FOR?
[MIZPHA] I GOT TIRED OF HIS
BLATHERING FOR ONE THING.
THE MORON SAID IT HIMSELF. DEATH
ISN'T PERMANENT FOR YOU TWO.
SERIOUSLY, WHEN I THINK ABOUT
ONE OF YOU ADVENTURERS
KICKING OFF...
YOU MIGHT AS WELL JUST BE SIMPLY
CHANGING ROOMS AT A HOTEL.
[NYANTA] GIRL, YOU'RE TRIPPIN'.
[MIZPHA] OH, PLEASE!
IT'S THE TRUTH, ISN'T IT?!
OH ANYWAY, WHERE ARE MY MANNERS?
I'M KNOWN AS MIZPHA TRUDE...
THE GENERAL CONQUEROR!
AND THAT MAKES ME THE
COMMANDING OFFICER HERE!
SO IT WAS YOU! YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO WENT AND HIRED
THAT FOOL LONDARK.
IS THIS HOW PEOPLE OF THE
LAND HANDLE THEIR BUSINESS?
(LAUGHS) SOMEONE LIKE YOU SHOULD
KNOW BETTER THAN THAT BY NOW!
"PEOPLE OF THE LAND"?
"ADVENTURERS"?
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE?
LIVING THINGS LIVE OFF THE
DEATH OF OTHER LIVING THINGS!
WE'RE THE STRONG, AND
OUR STRENGTH IS A WEAPON!
AND OF COURSE, THE WEAK USE
THEIR WEAKNESS TO GET WHAT
THEY WANT! THAT'S THE
TRUTH IN ANY WORLD!
[MIZPHA]
EHEH! HWAH!
YAHHHH!
HUAH!
[NYANTA, THINKING]
SHE'S NOT BAD!
HOW COULD A PERSON OF THE LAND
MASTER A SWORD LIKE THAT?!
[MIZPHA] WHAT RIGHT DOES
A PERSON WHO CAN'T DIE
HAVE QUESTIONING MY
DESIRES FOR DOMINATION.
[NYANTA]
YOU'RE INSTIGATING WAR. HWAH.
UYAH!
UH!
UGH...
[MIZPHA]
RAAAAGH!
GAHHH!
(GRUNT)
[MIZPHA] UYAH! CAN YOU FEEL IT?!
MY LIFE IS ABLAZE WITH GLORY!
I'M BURNING WITH
THE FIRE OF WAR!
NOW DANCE WITH ME, YOU ZOMBIE!
HWAH! HA...
[NYANTA]
"ZOMBIE"...?
[MIZPHA] WHAT ELSE
SHOULD I CALL A FREAK
WHO WON'T DIE!
[NYANTA]
SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
VIPER STRIKE RUSH!
[NYANTA] HWAH, HWAH!
[MIZPHA] OH...
[MIZPHA]
YAH!
IT'S BEAUTIFUL! YOU
REALLY ARE AMAZING!
I MEAN... I COULD REALLY
FALL FOR YOUR SKILL!
BUT I ALREADY KNOW YOU DON'T
HAVE THE STOMACH TO FINISH ME!
[NYANTA] YOU FIND AN
UNHEALTHY AMOUNT OF PRIDE
IN A SWORD FUELED BY MALICE!
[NYANTA] ZUWAH!
[MIZPHA] UGH!
EARLY BATTLE THRUST!
[MIZPHA] OHH...!
[NYANTA] ZUU...
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
[NYANTA] GUH!
HUH?
[NYANTA]
HUH? HUAH!
HUH?
[NYANTA] KAZUHIKO...
[DARIELLA] SPIRITUAL HYPNOTICS.
(CRIES, SCREAMS)
[NUREHA, THINKING]
THAT WAS STRANGE.
I MEAN ALL I WANTED TO DO
WAS TOY WITH THEM A BIT.
GAINING THEIR CONFIDENCE
SHOULD'VE BEEN SIMPLE.
I WAS FRIENDLY. I
SHOULD'VE FIT RIGHT IN.
ALL I HAD TO DO WAS
BE NICE TO THEM
AND THOSE CHILDREN
WARMED RIGHT UP TO ME.
IT SHOULD'VE BEEN
EASY AFTER THAT.
I THOUGHT SHIROE WAS
THE ONLY SPECIAL ONE
I'D EVER MEET. I GUESS
I WAS WRONG... AGAIN.
I THOUGHT THERE WAS NOTHING TO
THEM BEING IN THE SAME GUILD...
WRONG ABOUT THAT, TOO.
[TOYA] I'M JUST
NOT SURE ABOUT YOU.
'CAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS SMILING.
[DARIELLA] IF YOU THINK SO.
WHY WOULD YOU SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT TO ME?
[TOYA] YOU DON'T...
HAVE TO FAKE IT, YOU KNOW.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO...
NOT AROUND ANY OF US.
YOU CAN BE... WHOEVER YOU ARE.
[NUREHA, THINKING] HE MIGHT BE
YOUNG,
BUT THAT CHILD HAS A STRONG
AND MIGHTY SWORD FORGED
DEEP WITHIN HIS HEART.
[NUREHA] HM...
[NUREHA, THINKING]
YES! SHIROE'S TEACHINGS ARE
THE WEAPON HE GIVES OTHERS.
NOW I KNOW HOW
SPECIAL HE REALLY IS!
[LOREILE] PRINCESS NUREHA!
YOU'RE MAJESTY...!
IT'S NO LONGER SAFE
FOR YOU TO BE HERE!
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO TAKE
YOU BACK TO THE PALACE?
[NUREHA] WHAT HAPPENED
TO THIS PLACE?
NO ONE WILL BE ABLE
TO LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
WAS MIZPHA BEHIND THIS?
[LOREILE]
YES, MILADY!
[NUREHA]
I SEE...
[NUREHA, THINKING]
I ALLOWED HER TO DO THIS
BECAUSE I DIDN'T GIVE ANY
THOUGHT TO THE RESULTS.
I CAME OUT HERE AT HER REQUEST.
BUT TO SEE WHAT'S HAPPENED...
[NUREHA] ELIMINATE EVERY
WYVERN FROM THE SKY...
AND DESTROY THE NIGHTSHADE
SERVANTS ALONG WITH THEM.
HUH?
[LOREILE]
ARE YOU SURE, MILADY?
[NUREHA] YOUR CHIEF COUNCILOR
GAVE YOU AN ORDER.
[LOREILE]
OF COURSE!
[NUREHA, THINKING] MASTER
SHIROE, I'LL DO WHAT I CAN
TO GIVE YOUR JUNIOR MEMBERS
ALL THE HELP THEY NEED.
OUR TIME TOGETHER WAS SHORT,
BUT THEY EMBRACED ME WITH
WARMTH AS ONE OF THEIR OWN.
I WONDER IF YOU'LL
NOTICE WHAT I'M DOING...
WILL YOU THINK I'M
HINDERING THEM?
OR WILL YOU BE PLEASED?
I GUESS IT'S JUST ANOTHER
SILLY WHIM OF MINE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M
GIVING THEM A GIFT.
[DARIELLA, THINKING]
SO PLEASE, HURRY...
I WANT TO HEAR YOUR VOICE
ONE MORE TIME, SHIROE.
(HUMMING)
[KAZUHIKO] IT'S BEEN A
WHILE, CHIEF NYANTA...
THE TEA PARTY'S LONG SINCE GONE.
[NYANTA] OUT OF
THE WAY, KAZUHIKO!
I HAVE TO FINISH THIS
BEFORE IT GETS OUT OF CONTROL.
I THINK NOT. YOU'RE
NOT GETTING PAST ME.
WHY ARE YOU MIXED UP WITH
THESE PEOPLE OF THE LAND?
[KAZUHIKO]
MY SENSE OF DUTY, OF COURSE!
[NYANTA, THINKING] KAZUHIKO IS
WORKING TO TURN PLANT HWYADEN
INTO A HEALTHY AND
PRODUCTIVE GUILD.
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT
SHIROE‐ECCHI SAID.
BUT LOOKING AT HIM NOW,
IT'S OBVIOUS TO ME THAT KAZUHIKO
HAS LOST TOUCH WITH HIS
INNER SENSE OF WELL‐BEING.
THERE'S SO MUCH ANGER IN HIM
I CAN'T HELP BUT FEEL IT.
[MIZPHA] YAHH! YOU'RE GONNA
KILL ME WITH BOREDOM! RAH!
HWUH!
[MIZPHA] OPERATION: RED
NIGHT IS ALREADY UNDERWAY!
RED NIGHT WILL KNOCK YOU
ADVENTURERS OFF
OF YOUR LITTLE
PEDESTALS FOR GOOD!
IT'S TIME TO DIE...! NOT
THAT IT'LL BOTHER YOU!
(GRUNTING AND GROWLING)
UWAH!
(GRUNT, LAUGH)
MIZPHA!
[MIZPHA] YOU'RE DISAPPOINTING
ME, ADVENTURER!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GONNA BE STRONGER!
PHYSICALLY YOU ARE! BUT
ALL THAT COMPASSION
IS GOING TO GET YOU
KILLED ONE OF THESE DAYS!
AND YOU'LL END UP
GETTING OTHERS KILLED...
WITH YOUR RIDICULOUS
URGE TO SAVE THEIR LIVES.
HWUH! UYAHHHH
YES! THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I WANNA SEE!
(GROWLING)
[KAZUHIKO]
MIZPHA, PLAYTIME'S OVER.
[MIZPHA] YOU HAD NO
RIGHT TO DO THAT!
YOU'RE A WATCHDOG, KAZUHIKO!
[KAZUHIKO] THE PRINCESS HAS
GIVEN ME DIRECT ORDERS.
AND EVERYONE IN PLANT HWYADEN
IS GOING TO FOLLOW HER ORDERS
WHETHER THEY LIKE IT OR NOT!
[MIZPHA] UNNPH!
[KAZUHIKO] STAND DOWN! THIS
OPERATION IS BEING CANCELLED.
(IRRITATED GROWL)
[NYANTA] KAZUHIKO, WHAT IN THE
HELL IS PLANT HWYADEN DOING?
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE‐
I DON'T NEED TO
TELL YOU ANYTHING!
[KAZUHIKO] UWAH!
(NYANTA GRUNTING)
[KAZUHIKO, THINKING] THIS IS
BETTER THAN THE ALTERNATIVE.
(HARD EXHALE)
HYAH!
UGH! UH
HA‐HWAH
(EXPLOSION)
[KAZUHIKO, THINKING] NOW HE
WON'T HAVE THE BLOOD OF
A PERSON OF THE LAND
ON HIS HANDS.
[NYANTA, THINKING]
KAZUHIKO, DID YOU STEP IN
BECAUSE WE USED TO BE FRIENDS?
WELL, I'M GLAD TO SEE
YOU STILL CARE ABOUT ME.
[RUDY]
ORB OF LAVA!
[ISUZU]
UH‐HEHE
[RUDY]
UH?
HWAH!
[ISUZU]
UH... HUH?
[RUDY]
HUH? WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ISUZU]
ARE THOSE KIDS OVER THERE?
(STAGGER)
(COLLAPSE)
(SURPRISED GASPS)
[ISUZU, THINKING]
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING FOR THEM...
[TOYA]
UH?
[ROE2] MY LITTLE BROTHER
AND SISTER...
BIG SISTER'S HERE!
I WON'T ABANDON YOU!
THE FIRST FRIEND I MADE IN THIS
WORLD IS WORRIED THAT THERE
ISN'T GONNA BE ANYTHING LEFT
HERE BUT SADNESS AND SORROW!
UNABLE TO REACH AN
UNDERSTANDING,
HER KINGDOM WAS
LEFT TO COLLAPSE.
NOW THE PRINCESS IS
SCREAMING INSIDE OF ME!
WALK WITH ME, THE PRINCESS
WHO SHATTERS ALL COVENANTS!
DISRUPTOR OF ALL TREATIES!
SWORD PRINCESS AL QUENJE!
[RUDY] HUH?
[ISUZU] HM?
(SURPRISED GASP)
HUH?
(STRUMMING HARP)
(EXPLOSION)
[MINORI]
OH, WOW!
[RUDY] UH...
[ISUZU] UH?
[ISUZU, THINKING] I MIGHT NOT
BE ABLE TO HELP ANYONE TODAY.
NOT WITH THE ODDS WE'RE FACING.
BUT I'LL LEND YOU MY VOICE
AND MY STRINGS
TO LET YOU KNOW THAT
YOU'RE ALL IMPORTANT TO ME!
I'LL DO WHAT I CAN,
AND HOPE IT HELPS.
MUSIC IS SUCH A MINOR,
LITTLE THING...
IT CAN ONLY DO SO MUCH...
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW MUCH YOU
SING
ABOUT WANTING TO
CHANGE THE WORLD.
WE ALL HAVE TO PLAY A PART!
YOU CAN BE THE GREATEST
MUSICIAN THERE EVER WAS!
BUT SONGS, ON THEIR OWN, CAN'T
REALLY BRING PEACE TO THE WORLD.
AND THAT'S FINE...
BUT EVEN SO...
I'M GOING TO SING FOR YOU...
I KNOW WHAT MAKES YOU WHAT
YOU ARE AND I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE FEELING RIGHT
NOW... I REALLY DO!
SONGS ARE PRAYERS THAT
ARE HEARD AND ANSWERED!
I KNOW THE FEELING ALL TOO WELL.
MY FRIENDS, MY FAMILY WERE
ALWAYS TELLING ME
TO HANG IN THERE,
AND TO NOT GIVE UP.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL EVER
BECOME A MUSICIAN...
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THIS MUCH,
I SWEAR I'LL LOVE MUSIC EVERY
DAY FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE!
RUDY DID EVERYTHING HE COULD
TO BECOME AN ADVENTURER.
IT DIDN'T EVEN MATTER IF
IT WAS REALLY POSSIBLE...
HE FOUGHT AND HE FOUGHT AGAINST
THE INJUSTICES OF THE WORLD!
SO I GUESS I DON'T
REALLY NEED TO KNOW
IF I'M A NATURAL BORN
MUSICIAN OR NOT.
RUDY. HE BROUGHT ME
CLOSER TO MYSELF.
RUDY ALWAYS BELIEVED IN
ME... HE GAVE ME MY SONG!
[SERARA] ISUZU!
[BOTH] HUH?!
[RUDY] MISS SERARA!
[SERARA] EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
I DID A QUICK SEARCH
WEST OF HERE
TO GET ALL THE
PEOPLE OUT OF TOWN!
WOLFY HAS A REALLY GOOD NOSE!
HE MADE SURE WE WERE
ABLE TO FIND EVERYBODY
AND GET THEM
TO SAFETY.
[TOYA, VOICE CHAT] COME ON, MAN!
GIVE IT A REST! [ISUZU] TOYA...?
[SHUNICHI] MOVE IT, KID! I
TOLD YOU TO STAY OUT OF THIS!
THIS FIGHT IS FOR THE ODYSSEY
KNIGHTS. I DOESN'T CONCERN YOU!
[RUDY] IT SOUNDS LIKE
THEY'RE STILL GOING AT IT.
[ISUZU]
YEAH! AND TOYA'S NOT LETTING UP!
[SERARA] SOUNDS LIKE THEY'RE ON
THE BRIDGE... THEY'RE NEARBY.
[RUDY] DON'T SCREW IT UP
BEFORE I GET OUT THERE! OK?
I'M ON MY WAY!
[SERARA] C'MON...
[BOTH] MM‐HM
RUNDELLHAUS KODE TO THE RESCUE!
[TOYA]
I'M NOT BACKING DOWN!
GAH! (GRUNT)
LISTEN TO ME! THERE'S NO WAY I'M
JUST GONNA LET YOU
KILL YOURSELVES! YOU GOT THAT!
[SHUNICHI] I'M NOT TAKING THIS
FROM A SNOT‐NOSED LITTLE PUNK!
YOU BETTER GET OUTTA MY
WAY BOY...! DON'T MAKE ME DO
SOMETHING THAT WILL SEND
YOU TO THE CATHEDRAL.
YOU DO WHAT YOU
NEED TO DO! DO IT!
GO FOR IT! BUT I'M NOT MOVING!
[RUDY] TOYA!
(GETTING PUNCHED) (ALL GASPING)
(TOYA GRUNTING)
[SHUNICHI] YOU WON'T STOP THE
ODYSSEY KNIGHTS
FROM THEIR DESTINY...
CLEAR OUR PATH TO
THE UNDERWORLD!
[ISUZU] UH!
(QUICK BREATHS)
[RUDY] TOYA!
[ISUZU] THAT'S NOT TRUE!
[TOYA] HUH?
[ISUZU] YOU DON'T NEED A
STUPID "DYING GROUND"
OR SOME "PATH TO
THE UNDERWORLD..."
MISS ISUZU...?
[ISUZU] RUDY,
YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT TO DO?
I WANNA GIVE THIS
WORLD ITS 43RD SONG!
I WROTE IT FOR THIS WORLD...
AND I'M GONNA PLAY IT
RIGHT HERE AND NOW!
[BOTH] OHHH? (BREATH)
[TOYA] MMM.
[ISUZU, THINKING]
AFTER ALL, THIS IS THE WORLD...
... WHERE I WALK
ALONGSIDE MY FRIENDS.
I'LL ADMIT IT...
...IT'S NOT PERFECT...
FAR FROM IT.
BUT AT LEAST IT'S NOT
SOME DESPERATE PATH
TO SELF‐DESTRUCTION.
(MUSIC BEGINNING)
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
THEIR JOURNEY IS DONE.
WHAT DID THEY ACCOMPLISH?
WERE THEY ABLE TO SAVE ANYONE?
THE JUNIOR MEMBERS LEAVE WITH
A DARK CLOUD HANGING OVER THEM.
WHILE THEY ARE STILL TROUBLED
BY WHAT TRANSPIRED,
ROE2 GIVES THEM A LETTER
ADDRESSED TO SHIROE.
MEANWHILE, A NEW THREAT BEARS
DOWN ON THE CITY OF AKIHABARA.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.