[RIEZE]
YES, UNDERSTOOD...
LET ME SEE WHAT I
CAN FIND OUT HERE.
I'LL CALL BACK SHORTLY.
[HENRIETTA]
PARDON ME, MISS RIEZE..
(GASP)
UH?
[RIEZE]
I... I'M SORRY IT'S NOTHING.
I... I JUST KNOW THIS IS
A DESPERATE TIME FOR US.
MAYBE, BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
HIDE YOUR FEELINGS FROM US.
MPH...
AH...
[HENRIETTA] LOOK, IF YOU
WANNA TALK ABOUT IT,
I DON'T MIND BEING HERE FOR
YOU, OKAY?
MM. (SNIFFLE)
(STREET CHATTER)
[HENRIETTA] MISA'S SCYTHE
WENT OUT OF CONTROL?!
AND WHAT? IT MADE KRUSTY
VANISH INTO THIN AIR?
[RIEZE] NONE OF US CAN GET OUT
TELEPATHIC CALLS TO GO THROUGH.
AND WE STILL HAVE TO DEAL WITH
THIS SERIAL KILLER MENACE.
IF THERE'S ONE THING WE NEED TO
KEEP UNDER CONTROL, IT'S THAT
WE DON'T WANT ANY INFORMATION
ABOUT THIS TO GET OUT.
YES, YOU MIGHT WANNA KEEP THIS
FROM THE ROUND TABLE.
THE TIMING WOULD NOT BE IDEAL.
WE STILL DON'T KNOW WHO
MINAMI'S SPIES ARE.
I'M WONDERING
IF WE SHOULD
INFORM PRINCESS
RAYNESHIA OR NOT.
DEFINITELY.
AND IF I KNOW KRUSTY
LIKE YOU DO, RIEZE,
HE'LL WALTZ RIGHT BACK TO US
AS IF NOTHING HAPPENED AT ALL.
I SUPPOSE HE WOULD.
(PING)
[HENRIETTA] MPH.
[MIKAKAGE, VOICE CHAT]
HENRIETTA, THIS IS HORRIBLE!
WHAT'S GOING ON MIKAKAGE?
[MIKAKAGE]
THERE'S SOMETHING VERY WRONG
WITH THE FLAVOR TEXTS!
MPH....
[RIEZE] THINGS ARE LITERALLY
BECOMING THEIR DESCRIPTIONS?
[MIKAKAGE] YEAH. EVEN THOUGH
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN THERE
JUST TO ADD AMBIANCE
AND INTRIGUE.
BUT NOW, ANYTHING WRITTEN
IN THE FLAVOR TEXT
IS BECOMING TRUE TO LIFE.
WELL, I GUESS THAT MEANS
WE'LL NEED TO PAY MUCH CLOSER
ATTENTION TO ALL THE ITEM
DESCRIPTIONS FROM NOW ON.
IT COULD START CAUSING ALL KINDS
OF TROUBLE FOR US IF WE DON'T.
[RIEZE, THINKING]
THE FLAVOR TEXT, WORDS GIVING
THEIR OBJECTS UNFORESEEN POWER.
MAYBE THAT'S THE REASON MISA'S
WEAPON ATTACKED HER AND KRUSTY.
TO COMPLICATE MATTERS...
[RIEZE] THE KILLER IS IN
POSSESSION OF BYAKUMARU.
WHO KNOWS WHAT WILL HAPPEN IF
THE FLAVOR TEXT OF THAT
SWORD WERE TO COME TO LIFE!
[BOTH] HUH?
THAT SWORD CAN DO AN INCREDIBLE
AMOUNT OF DAMAGE ON IT'S OWN.
NOW IT'S IN THE HANDS OF
SOMEONE IN ROYAL GUARD ARMOR.
IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
YOU GET BYAKUMARU AS
AN ITEM DROP IN A QUEST.
THAT'S RIGHT, IT'S
ONE OF THE RAIDS
THEY RELEASED IN
EXPANSION‐PACK TEN.
YOU HAD TO BEAT THE DEAD
WARRIOR LUGRIUS TO GET IT.
[RIEZE] IT WAS HIS SWORD, AND
IT WAS ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
DEAD WARRIOR LUGRIUS?
[HENRIETTA] SO WHAT
DOES THE FLAVOR TEXT
ON LUGRIUS HAVE TO SAY?
[RIEZE] IT TALKS
ABOUT THE LEGEND
OF LUGRIUS AND HOW HE
TURNED INTO A DEMON.
LUGRIUS ORIGINALLY FOUGHT AS
THE HERO OF THE ICY WALLS
ALONG SIDE THE IZUMO KNIGHTS
FOR A HUNDRED YEARS.
IT'S SAID THAT HE FOUGHT
LONG AND HARD TO DEFEND
THE HEALTH AND HAPPINESS
OF THE SUSUKINO PEOPLE ALWAYS
KEEPING THE EVIL GIANTS AT BAY.
HE WAS TRULY THE EZZO
EMPIRE'S CHAMPION.
HOWEVER...
HOWEVER, THE MAID
OF ELM, SUTUYNAW,
SERVED LUGRIUS
A DEADLY POISON
IN AN UNFORESEEN
ACT OF BETRAYAL.
SHORTLY AFTER,
HE BECAME A MONSTER
FILLED WITH BITTERNESS
AND HATRED FOR EVERYONE.
WELL THAT CERTAINLY DOESN'T
PAINT A BRIGHT LIGHT ON THINGS.
DO YOU THINK THE
EVIL SPIRIT IS REAL?
AND THAT HE'S OUT THERE HELPING
THE KILLER IN THE ARMOR?
[RIEZE]
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
[MIKAKAGE] HUH?
(HENRIETTA GASPS)
[RIEZE] I'M TERRIBLY
SORRY ABOUT THAT... I ...
I GUESS MAYBE IT COULD BE,
AND THAT COULD POSSIBLY HELP US
DEVISE A PLAN TO DEFEAT LUGRIS.
[BOTH]
OHHH?
(EXHALE)
(GROANING)
[NERURESU, VOICE STRAINING]
GET OUT OF MY HEAD!
DAMN YOU... I WON'T
BE YOUR PUPPET!
I'M A MEMBER OF
THE ROYAL GUAAAARD!
[LUGRIUS, TAKING OVER NERURESU'S
VOICE] RELEASE YOURSELF,
YOU'RE NOT THIS TOWN'S
FILTHY GUARD DOG.
WITH POWER GREATER
THAN THE ADVENTURERS,
YOU SHOULD BE THEIR HERO.
JOIN ME IN MY VENGEANCE
AGAINST THE MAID OF ELM.
AGAINST ALL THE PUTRID HUMAN
REFUSE SWIMMING AROUND YOU!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
FLAVOR TEXT IS COMING TO LIFE.
I WONDER, WHAT WOULD'VE HAPPENED
IF I'D BEEN ABLE TO GET
BYAKUMARU BEFORE THE KILLER DID?
I WAS SO JEALOUS OF MINORI
WHO KNOWS WHAT I WOULD'VE DONE
WITH ALL THAT HATE IN ME?
(INHALE, SIGH)
MPH.
(MUNCH)
[NAZNA]
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
UH‐HUH?
I THINK IT'D BE BEST IF I
STAYED OUT OF IT FOR NOW.
BESIDES, I'M SURE MASTER
SHIROE'S GUILDMATE
WILL FIND A
SOLUTION SOON ENOUGH.
SO IT REALLY DOES BOIL
DOWN TO ORAL ARTS?
HM...
THANK YOU.
THE ORAL ARTS ARE QUITE SIMPLE.
(SIPS)
AND AS FOR ME, I HAVE THE
POWER OF MY GIRLS BY MY SIDE.
(EXHALE)
[NAZNA] ALL RIGHT,
WE ALL KNOW THE GOAL
FOR OUR NEW
TRAINING SESSIONS.
FIND AND DESTROY THE SERIAL
KILLER TERRORIZING OUR CITY.
IN KEEPING WITH
RIEZE'S STRATEGY,
THE TRAINING SESSIONS WILL HELP
EVERYONE GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER
AS WELL AS INCREASE YOUR
ABILITIES IN BATTLE.
AND THIS ONE HERE, SHE SAYS SHE
WANTS TO LEARN THE ORAL ARTS.
[AKATSUKI] UH...?
[NAZNA] SO I NEED YOU TO SHOW
HER EVERYTHING YOU'VE
PICKED UP SO FAR.
UH... I'M NOT ALL THAT SKILLED,
BUT YOU HAVE MY FULL DEVOTION!
(LAUGHING) YOU MIGHT
WANNA SAVE THAT
FOR THE GUY YOU END UP MARRYING!
(LAUGHTER) [MIKAKAGE] HENRIETTA
WOULD HAVE LOST HER MIND IF
SHE HEARD YOU SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
(GIGGLING)
[CHIKA] YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY
ONE WHO WANTS TO TOUGHEN UP.
UH...
[SANDY]
MPH...
[KYOKO]
LET'S GET STARTED THEN,
AND TAKE 'EM OUT!
(HAPPY MURMURS/CLAPPING)
[AKATSUKI] OH...
AREN'T YOU GLAD YOU DECIDED
TO COME OUT AND JOIN US?
[AKATSUKI] MM‐HM.
[NAZNA] YOU KNOW
THE DRILL, PEOPLE!
[NAZNA] FIRST IS TO
ACCURATELY JUDGE DISTANCES!
[NAZNA] FIND YOUR RANGE!
[SANDY] GET OUTTA THE WAY!
[KOZARU] I'M NOT REALLY SURE
WHAT ELSE I CAN SAY ABOUT IT.
ANYTHING YOU CAN,
EVERYTHING HELPS!
[YUTA] HMMM...
YOU CAN'T JUST GO
AND LEARN AN ORAL ART
BY CLEARING A RAID,
AND IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S
AND ITEM DROP
FROM KILLING AN
ENEMY OR ANYTHING.
HE'S RIGHT YOU KNOW,
I MEAN THEY'RE REALLY
NOT ALL THAT SPECIAL
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT 'EM.
[KOZARU] EVEN IF I TOLD
YOU HOW I GOT ONE,
YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO DO THE SAME THING.
AH, EH... FOR EXAMPLE,
OUR GUILD MASTER LEARNED
HOW TO USE "HYPERION EYE."
WE CAN ALL LEARN WHAT IT DOES,
BUT NOT NECESSARILY MASTER IT.
[AKATSUKI] MM‐HM.
EVEN IF HE DOESN'T HAVE A
GOOD LOOK AT HIS TARGET,
HE STILL HAS THE ABILITY
TO DETERMINED WHAT
IT'S HIT POINTS AND STATUS ARE.
SO IF YOU WERE ABLE TO
MASTER SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
YOU CAN FIGURE OUT HOW
MANY HIT POINTS THE GUYS
BEHIND YOU HAVE AND FIGURE
OUT IF THEY'RE A THREAT.
IT'S ACTUALLY PRETTY SWEET!
THAT WOULD BE VERY HELPFUL.
[KOZARU]
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
HE'S THE ONLY PERSON WE
KNOW WHO CAN USE IT.
[AKATSUKI] UH...?
THERE IS NO GUARANTEE
YOU CAN MASTER IT.
EVEN IF YOU LEARN
THE FIRST LEVEL.
(EXHALES)
I'LL TAKE WHAT I CAN GET!
PLEASE HELP ME!
(FIGHTING NOISES)
[BOTH] HYAH!
[AKATSUKI]
UH!
UH?!
(GROAN)
[YUTA] MM.
[KOZARU] HWAH.
(STRUGGLING)
[AKATSUKI]
LET'S TRY IT AGAIN!
UH?
MMM... (SIGH)
(LUNCH CHATTER)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] ORAL ARTS.
PLEASE SHOW ME
SOME SORT OF CLUE.
[MIKAKAGE]
HEY, AKATSUKI!
HUH?
I MADE SOMETHING FOR
YOU... IT'S SPECIAL.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN IT'S SPECIAL?
(BOTH GIGGLE)
[AKATSUKI]
HUH?
OH‐UH, UH... (PLEASANT SIGH)
[HENRIETTA] OUR KILLER IS A
MEMBER OF THE ROYAL GUARD.
HE IS A PERSON OF THE LAND IN
POSSESSION OF MOVABLE ARMOR...
AND HE IS ARMED WITH THE SWORD
OF THE COLD, BYAKUMARU.
IT'S USUAL ATTACK IS BLIZZARD
AND FREEZE AND IT CAN INFLICT
ITS DAMAGE AT GREAT
RANGE ON ITS TARGET.
I REMEMBER HIM. WASN'T
LUGRIUS A RAID BOSS?
YES. AND KNOWING THAT
SHOULD HELP US DEFEAT HIM.
ASSUMING THE FLAVOR TEXT
HOLDS TRUE FOR BOTH,
IT SHOULD ENLIGHTEN
US IN THREE WAYS.
FIRST, THE SWORD
WILL USE BLIZZARD
TO INFLICT THE FREEZE
STATUS EFFECT.
SECOND, IT WILL INCREASE ALL OF
THE STATS OF THE PERSON
WITH THE SWORD, MULTIPLIED
BY HIS OPPOSITION.
EVERY OFFENSIVE AND DEFENSIVE
STATISTIC FOR BYAKUMARU'S MASTER
WILL GO UP FOR EVERY PLAYER THAT
OPPOSES HIM WITHIN FIFTY METERS.
AHHH... (SIGH)
MEANING THAT OVERWHELMING HIM
WITH NUMBERS ISN'T GONNA WORK.
THAT'S WHERE OUR STRATEGY COMES
IN. IT'S STILL POSSIBLE TO USE
A RAID PARTY IN THIS SITUATION,
BUT WITH A DIFFERENT TACTIC.
WE STILL USE OUR TWENTY‐FOUR,
WITH THE USUAL SIX SPLIT IN TWO
OR THREE, BUT SCATTERED ACROSS
THE CITY LIKE A NET.
YOU WANT TO HOLD A FULL
RAID INSIDE THE CITY.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
PRETTY AMAZING, RIEZE.
YOU CAN TELL SHE'S IN CHARGE OF
THE DEVELOPMENT AND TRAINING
SQUADRON IN KRUSTY'S GUILD.
SHE'S SHOWING NO SIGNS OF
WILTING OR BACKING DOWN
IN THE FACE OF ALL
THE GRAND WARRIORS.
IT SEEMS TO ME THAT YOU'RE
SPREADING YOUR TEAM OUT TOO FAR.
HOW DO YOU PLAN TO LEAD THEM?
WE'LL USE THE TELEPATHIC NETWORK
TO KEEP OUR CHAT UP AND
RUNNING DURING THE BATTLE.
ONCE ONE OF THE GROUPS MAKES
CONTACT, WE'LL HAVE THEM
DEPLOYED IN SUCH A WAY THAT THE
OTHERS CAN GET TO THEM QUICKLY.
[WOODSTOCK] SO I'M GUESSING
BYAKUMARU'S THIRD AFFECT ISN'T
HARD TO GUESS, AM I RIGHT?
[SOJIRO] HUH?
RIGHT, LIKE A LOT OF MAGIC
SWORDS WE ALREADY KNOW ABOUT.
THERE SHOULD BE A BASIC BOOST
TO HIS HIT‐POINTS...
OF COURSE WE STILL NEED TO DEAL
WITH HIS OPPOSITION INCREASE.
[WOODSTOCK] I SWEAR, I DON'T
KNOW WHO CAME UP WITH THAT,
BUT I'VE ALWAYS HATED IT.
HOW DO YOU PLAN TO DEAL WITH IT?
WE NEED PERMISSION
FOR A CURFEW.
AND WE NEED IT FROM RIGHT NOW
UNTIL MIDNIGHT NEW YEAR'S DAY.
IT SHOULD COME FROM THE ROUND
TABLE TO ASK ALL THE PEOPLE OF
THE LAND TO STAY IN THEIR
HOMES FOR THEIR OWN SAFETY.
WELL THAT'S CERTAINLY
A START I GUESS...
DO YOU REALLY THINK WE SHOULD
FACE SOMETHING SO POWERFUL?
WOODSTOCK HAS A POINT.
IF THE KILLER HAS A
GUARDSMAN'S MOVEABLE ARMOR,
THEN HE CAN TELEPORT ANYWHERE
WITHIN THE CITY AT ANY TIME!
IT WILL ALL BE A WASTE
IF HE GETS AWAY!
WE HAVE A SOLUTION. BUT WE NEED
THE PRINCESS TO MAKE IT WORK!
HUH?
(GASP)
[RAYNESHIA] SO YOU'RE TELLING
ME, YOU WANT ME TO CUT THE POWER
TO AKIHABARA'S
MAGIC CIRCLE, RIGHT?
(UNCERTAIN BREATH)
[KINJO] WE CAN DEPRIVE
THE ARMOR OF ITS POWER
BY SHUTTING OFF THE MAGIC
TO THE CITY'S CIRCLE.
OF COURSE, THIS WOULD ALSO
NEUTRALIZE THE CITY'S
OTHER MAGICAL DEFENSES.
THERE WOULD BE NOTHING STOPPING
MONSTERS FROM COMING IN.
WELL, IF YOU WERE TO TRY THIS?
COULDN'T YOU JUST RESTORE
THE CIRCLE RIGHT
AFTER HE'S ELIMINATED?
I'M AFRAID IT'S NOT THAT
SIMPLE, YOUR GRACE.
IT WOULD TAKE
DECADES TO RESTORE.
(EXHALE)
[RIEZE] I'M ALREADY AWARE
THIS PLAN HAS ITS RISKS.
LISTEN TO ME, RAYNESHIA. I KNOW
THIS CANNOT BE AN EASY DECISION.
BUT WITH YOUR BLESSING
WE DO HAVE A CHANCE.
NO! I KNOW IT WILL WORK!
SO ARE YOU ASKING ME THIS AS A
TASK OF MY OFFICIAL POSITION?
AS AN EMISSARY OF MY PEOPLE?
[HENRIETTA]
FOR SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
WE CAN'T DO IT ANY OTHER WAY.
(EXHALE)
I RESPECT YOUR DECISION,
NO MATTER WHICH CHOICE
YOU END UP MAKING.
YEAH, ABSOLUTELY!
NOTHING'LL CHANGE BETWEEN ANY OF
US NO MATTER WHAT.
WHATEVER YOU DECIDE DON'T
BE AFRAID OF THAT.
(EXHALE)
(SIGH)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] IN THE
END, I COULDN'T BRING MYSELF TO
MAKE A DECISION RIGHT
THERE ON THE SPOT.
(GROANING)
I WANTED TO BE A FRIEND AND
GIVE THEM EVERYTHING
THEY ASKED OF ME.
BUT AS MY GRANDFATHER'S
AMBASSADOR...
WHAT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO?
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] OKAY, TIME
IS RUNNING SHORT,
SO WHAT DO I DO NOW?
[NYANTA]
HOW'S THE TRAINING GOING, MYAH?
OH...
SO WHEN'S THE BIG RAID
PARTY IN THE CITY, BABY?
NEW YEAR'S EVE.
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT?
TAKING CARE OF YOUR RESOLUTION
BEFORE THE END OF THE YEAR?
THAT'S COOL.
NOT SURE IF I'LL EVEN
MASTER AN ORAL ART,
IT'S LIKE I'M CONSTANTLY
GRASPING AT AIR.
I KNOW IT'S LATE, BUT IS
THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO
TO MAYBE HELP YOU
OUT A LITTLE BIT?
[AKATSUKI] THANKS FOR ASKING,
CHIEF, BUT I'M ALL RIGHT.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
I'M GETTING THE FEELING THAT
YOU'RE PUSHING YOURSELF
A LITTLE TOO HARD FOR
YOUR OWN GOOD, Y'KNOW.
[AKATSUKI]
OH...?
MY LORD, WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TAKING A BREAK FOR A WHILE?
I'M FINE, I NEED TO SQUEEZE IN
AS MUCH WORK AS I POSSIBLY CAN.
MAYBE, BUT DON'T OVERDO IT OKAY?
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT ME,
I'M WORKING HARD
BECAUSE I WANT TO.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHY MY
LORD PUSHES HIMSELF AS MUCH
AS HE DOES ALL THE TIME...
I MEAN I GUESS, HE'S TRYING TO
GET THE BEST OUT OF HIMSELF.
SO I WILL DO WITH
SAME THING FOR ME.
IF I WANT TO TAKE DOWN
AN ENEMY LIKE THIS,
I NEED TO TEST MY LIMITS.
IT'S ... IT'S JUST...
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
[NAZNA] COME ON YOU GUYS! KEEP
YOUR DISTANCE.
NOW! SLIP IN BEHIND YOUR ENEMY!
YOU NEED TO BE IN
A CONSTANT STATE
OF EVALUATING YOUR OPPONENT.
KNOW WHAT YOU CAN DO AND BE
AWARE OF WHAT YOU CANNOT DO,
SO IT DOESN'T TAKE YOU BY
SURPRISE IN THE FIGHT.
MM.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I KNOW THAT I'M WEAK...
BUT THERE ARE SOME THINGS
I CAN ONLY LEARN
BY KNOWING WHAT
MY WEAKNESSES ARE.
(SCREAM)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I'VE LEARNED FROM DEFEAT,
AND FOUND A PURPOSE
IN MY LACK OF TALENT.
(STRUGGLING)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
BUT STILL,
I CAN'T DO EVERYTHING MY OWN...
WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY
USING THIS, AKATSUKI?!
IT REALLY HELPS YOU
BUILD UP YOUR DEFENSES
HUH?! THANKS A
LOT, YOU GUYS.
I BET YOU'D LIKE TO HAVE A FEW
STRAWBERRIES, WOULDN'T YA?
[AKATSUKI] UH...
[DOLCHE] WE GOT A BUTT‐LOAD FOR
OUR CHRISTMAS CAKE AND HAD
A FEW LEFT OVER. MM‐MMM!
[AKATSUKI] UH... THANK YOU!
[KAWARA] EHEE!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] I CAN LEARN
TEAMWORK
AND GET STRONG AT THE SAME TIME!
[NAZNA] Y'KNOW,
YOU SURE ARE TINY.
LEARN TO USE IT
TO YOUR ADVANTAGE.
[AKATSUKI] HUH?
THINK ABOUT HOW BIG HE IS.
IT'LL DRIVE HIM NUTS IF YOU
KEEP MOVING AROUND
AND HE CAN'T HIT YOU.
HE SHOULD HAVE A
TON OF BLIND SPOTS.
COME ON, THEN. GIVE IT A TRY.
(GROWL)
(GRUNT)
[RICHO] HUH? (GRUNTS)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] UNTIL NOW,
I THOUGHT BEING SMALL
WAS ALWAYS WORKING AGAINST ME.
[RICHO] HWAH!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] BUT I CAN
ALSO USE IT TO MY ADVANTAGE.
(SCREAM) [AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I STILL NEED TO BE MINDFUL
OF WHAT I CAN AND
CANNOT DO, THOUGH
(RUNNING, SEINE
STRUGGLING BEHIND)
[BYAKKOU] THIS IS IT!
THIS IS THE PLACE! [ALL] HUH?
[BYAKKOU] IS THIS THE GUILD
TRAINING FOR THE MISSION
TO TAKE OUT THE SERIAL KILLER?
MICHITAKA TOLD US
ABOUT YOU GUYS.
WE THOUGHT WE'D COME
BY AND OFFER OUR HELP!
YOU'RE STILL LOOKING FOR MORE
RECRUITS RIGHT?
WE MOST DEFINITELY ARE, SO UH.
WOULD YOUR FRIEND
LIKE TO JOIN US?
[SEINE]
UH... YES, MA'AM.
[SEINE] HWAH!
[ALL] OHHHHH
[SEINE] AH NO... IT'S
REALLY NOTHING YOU GUYS.
LOOKS LIKE WE GOT
ALL THE POSITIONS
IN THE RAID PARTY FILLED.
NOW THAT WE'RE ALL SET...
CAN YOU TEND TO THAT OTHER
MATTER
AS MEMBER NUMBER TWENTY‐FIVE?
YOU BET, I'M ON IT.
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNT)
(FIGHTING NOISES)
(GROWL)
[MIKAKAGE] PRINCESS RAYNESHIA,
I'M GLAD YOU CAME OUT!
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU!
[RAYNESHIA] MM‐HM.
[AOMORI] MIKAKAGE, ARE
THE RICE BALLS READY YET?
[MIKAKAGE] OH, YEAH! IT'S
ALREADY NOON, ISN'T IT?
[AOMORI] YOU NEED TO BE A
LITTLE MORE AWARE, OKAY?!
THEY'RE NEVER GONNA BE READY IN
TIME UNLESS YOU HIT THE KITCHEN!
[MIKAKAGE] AW, SORRY!
[RAYNESHIA] UH, EXCUSE ME! DO
YOU THINK I COULD HELP YOU GUYS?
HUH? YOU WANNA HELP?
DO YOU HAVE THE COOKING
SKILL, YOUR HIGHNESS?
HUH? UH... I COULDN'T SAY.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO
GIVE IT A SHOT!
[KYOKO] I'M SO HUNGRY
I COULD EAT MY FOOT!
[DOLCHE]
LET'S DIG IN GUYS!
[ALL] THANKS FOR THE RICE BALLS!
(GIGGLE)
[DOLCHE] I'M GONNA STUFF MY FACE
WITH THESE BIG OL' YUMMY BALLS.
(EXHALES)
(MUNCH, CHEWS, EXHALES)
[RAYNESHIA]
IS ANYONE SITTING HERE?
OH...?
GO AHEAD.
YOU KNOW, I ACTUALLY
MADE THAT ONE.
HUH? (MUNCH)
IT'S LOPSIDED, BUT
GOOD. VERY TASTY.
WELL I'M GLAD YOU LIKE IT. HEH.
[RAYNESHIA]
I NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
I LOOKED AT YOU AS AN EASY
WAY OUT OF MY SITUATION.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
THE OTHER DAY, WHEN
YOU WENT OUT ON YOUR OWN
AND ATTEMPTED TO TAKE OUT
THE SERIAL KILLER FOR ME.
I WAS THINKING FOR A MOMENT
THAT IF YOU THAT IF YOU...
THAT IF YOU COULD HAVE DEFEATED
HIM THAT NIGHT THEN...
I MIGHT HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO AVOID ANY CONFLICT
BETWEEN MY PEOPLE AND YOURS.
I JUST WANTED TO CRY TO
MY GRANDFATHER
OR GET MASTER KRUSTY
TO HANDLE IT.
BUT YOU KNOW, I'M NOT GOING
TO BE THAT PERSON ANY MORE.
I'M NOT GOING TO AVOID
RESPONSIBILITY LIKE THE KUNIE
TRIBE, WHO LAID THE WHOLE THING
AT MY FEET A COUPLE DAYS AGO.
THAT SAID. I'M STILL
NERVOUS ABOUT IT.
AND I CAN'T DECIDE YET.
[AKATSUKI] IT MADE ME HAPPY
WHEN YOU SAID I WAS YOUR FRIEND.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE NERVOUS.
YOU HAVE A WHOLE LOT OF FRIENDS
HERE, WHO'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
PLUS ME, YOU KNOW... WE'RE STILL
FRIENDS! AND WE ALWAYS WILL BE!
THANKS AKATSUKI...
[NAZNA] LET'S GET THIS
SHOW ON THE ROAD, PEOPLE!
COMING!
WE'RE FRIENDS...
(COLLAPSE)
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK...? HAVE
YOU FIGURED ANYTHING OUT YET?
[AKATSUKI]
NN‐NMM
[NAZNA]
TO DISCOVER AN ORAL ART,
YOU MUST REALIZE YOU
DON'T ACTUALLY NEED IT.
[AKATSUKI] HWUUAAH? WHAT'S
THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?!
UH...
IF I HAD KNOWN...
I NEVER WOULD HAVE
SOLD IT TO HIM.
[RIEZE] THERE'S NO WAY
YOU COULD KNOW. IT'S FINE.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] I WILL NOT
RUN FROM THIS RESPONSIBILITY...
IF I DO THINGS
THE WAY I USED TO,
LETTING OTHER PEOPLE
FIGHT MY BATTLES FOR ME,
I'LL BE SHOWING EVERYONE THAT
I CAN NEVER BE TRUSTED WITH
THE WORK THAT BEFITS MY TITLE.
AND I COULD NEVER BE
WORTHY OF THEIR FRIENDSHIP!
(KNOCKING)
(DOOR OPENING)
[HENRIETTA] UH...
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA!
I NEED TO HAVE A
PART IN THIS QUEST!
PERHAPS AS THE TWENTY SIXTH
MEMBER OF THE SUIFUU MAIDENS,
WILL THAT DO?
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] IN THE END,
I HAVE FAILED TO MASTER
A SINGLE ORAL ART.
BUT THAT'S OKAY...
I NOW HAVE A TEAM I TRUST!
TAKE CARE OF
YOURSELVES OUT THAT.
NOW GIVE IT ALL YOU GOT!
[ALL] YEAH!
[DOLCHE] YOU GO GIRL!
NEW YEAR'S EVE IS HERE.
MM.
TIME TO GIVE HIM
THE END HE DESERVES.
(SURPRISED GASP)
[NERURESU]
YOU'RE KIDDING ME...
(INHALE)
YOU'RE NOT TAKING ME VERY
SERIOUSLY... JUST TWO OF YOU?
WELL, TIME TO DIE...
(GASP)
YOU'LL BE BOWING ON
YOUR HANDS AND KNEES
LIKE ALL THE OTHER COMMONERS...
BEFORE I TAKE THEIR LIVES.
JUST LIKE THE MAID OF ELM, YOU
WILL PAY FOR YOUR BETRAYAL!
YOU DON'T DESERVE TO LIVE!
LET'S GO!
HMPH!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
THE RAID IS UNDERWAY!
THE MURDERER'S SWORD SHINES
WITH THE POWER OF A BLIZZARD.
THE CONVICTION OF TWENTY‐SIX
COMRADES DRIVES THE FIGHT.
BUT FATE CAN BE A
FLICKERING FLAME.
JUST AS THE CITY
SINKS INTO DESPAIR,
A TWENTY‐SEVENTH MAIDEN
APPEARS WITH A MIGHTY WEAPON!
AND A PROFOUND SECRET
IS FINALLY DISCOVERED.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!